JEFF PROBST:
16 Americans forced
to abandon ship
in the middle
of the South China Sea.
Marooned for 39 days
they must work together
to build shelter,
find food
and survive the island.
But ultimately, it is
everyone for themselves.
Every third night, they will
hike deep into the jungle
to take part
in the Tribal Council
where they must vote one
of their own off the island.
In the end, only one will remain
and will leave the island
with $1 million in cash.
Last week on Survivor...
B.B's anger
with the Pagong Tribe
reached a fevered pitch.
I've been working
my ass off.
A lot of you have been
laying on your ass watching me.
Put the carrying log--
we're right in...
all the way over now.
If we're building a health gym,
I'll let you do it.
Damn it. Walk
straight in.
It may not be that right,
but how many times we got
to make those decisions?
JEFF:
At Tagi, the conflict
between Stacey and Rudy
deepened.
RUDY:
Me and her wouldn't get along.
If we were friends
on the outside
I'd definitely avoid her.
STACEY:
We've all seen him
eating extra food,
and he's just sort of
a liability to us.
He was sitting around
barking orders
and not really helping out much.
RUDY:
She's too prim-like, you know.
I mean, uh,
after about three weeks
out here in this jungle
she's going to learn a lesson,
I think.
JEFF:
And Richard shared openly
with his tribe mates.
There is a lifestyle
associated with being gay,
but you can't say
I decided to be gay.
RUDY:
The homosexual, he's one
of the nicest guys I ever met.
Me and Richard got to be
pretty good friends--
not in a homosexual way,
that's for sure.
JEFF:
At the immunity challenge,
Stacey pulled through
by winning
the final unappetizing round...
SEAN:
Swallow!
JEFF:
Tagi!
...forcing Pagong
to take the long hike
to the Tribal Council
where B.B.'S
volatile personality
finally caught up with him.
"B.B."
B.B., the tribe
has spoken.
It's time
for you to go.
All right.
JEFF:
14 Are left.
Tonight, one more will go.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
KELLY:
I keep forgetting
where I am...
when I wake up.
The plan now is to go out
and try to do
some early morning fishing.
SEAN:
Fishing is horrible.
That saying, "There's
a lot of fish in the sea"?
Not this sea.
They apparently didn't grow up
in Palua Tiga,
uh, because there is nothing
to be caught out there.
SUSAN:
As far as
the food holding up, uh,
I don't... I think
we're into day seven.
I lost track, but I know
it's starting to whittle down.
I know we got to get fish
in here.
( conch shell being blown )
SUSAN:
You want to check
the one on the left first?
KELLY AND STACEY:
We're going by that first.
KELLY:
Come on,
fish in the trap.
Rocks do not want to take
her down on that one end.
Okay.
Nothing.
Bait's all gone.
KELLY:
This is frustrating.
I mean, it's the ocean.
You think you'd get a fish
somehow, but no luck so far.
We all thought, "Oh, yeah,
you know, we got these traps,
we got hooks, we got a raft."
You know, there's no reason
why we shouldn't be having
big, fat fish for dinner
every night,
but we're just not.
To me, that's kind of like
uh, yeah, whoo-hoo,
big survivors, you know?
When was the last time
Rudy went on a water run?
He never did, did he?
I don't think
he's been
on a water run.
He's sneaky.
He is.
He swipes food
while he's in there
cooking in the kitchen.
STACEY:
I think we've all sort of
come to the conclusion
that Rudy really needs
to get out of here.
He just criticizes
whatever we're doing.
He's hurting morale.
We row out yesterday morning
and set the traps.
I come into the kitchen.
"Morning, Rudy,
how are you doing?"
"You're wasting your time
out there.
It's just a waste."
I was, like, "Damn,
morning to you, too."
What the hell.
SUSAN:
Well, he's wasting his time
by doing nothing, though.
KELLY:
I think we were all
kind of stoked that, you know,
yeah, he's an ex-Navy Seal,
We're going to kick ass.
But he really hasn't
contributed very much.
I think it's definitely
going to influence me
the next time I go
to Tribal Council.
I think it's influencing
all of us, you know.
When it comes down, you know,
to-to voting people
that we do like off, I...
it's sucky, but I think
it's going to come down
to whoever screws up
at the challenges.
SUSAN:
Yeah, 'cause I already
know who I'd vote for.
The person that's least
contributing to the group...
out of here.
I have conflicts--
personality conflicts
every day with people.
I deal with them, I work with
them, I live with them, I go on.
I'm going to do
the same thing here:
I'm going to get rid
of the weakest member
and vote Stacey out.
Stacey's trying to buddy up
with everybody
because she knows
she's the weakest.
STACEY:
When Kelly, Sue and I
were on the raft
we talked about
who we'd vote off.
Sue initially didn't want
to talk about it,
which immediately clued me in
that she was planning
to vote me off,
even though we decided
to stick together.
So now I don't trust her
as far as I can throw her,
which, according to the group,
would be not far.
Did you catch
anything?
SUSAN:
No fish.
We set the
traps up though.
Set the fish traps?
That's it?
Just... yeah, no fish.
We didn't fish
but 20 minutes.
COLLEEN:
The oomph is a little gone
from our group.
I don't know why that is.
I think that not eating
is a factor of our mood.
We want food.
Gretchen, Colleen and Greg,
they were out looking
for tapioca
so that we could have
mashed-potato style
tapioca root.
It's tapioca, for sure.
( all chuckling )
Just take a bite,
and see what...
No. Maybe it's just tapioca
run wild.
( chuckling )
Operation Tapioca has everything
to do with finding tapioca,
but we find other things
on the way, too.
COLLEEN:
The first time I came upon
the mud volcano
was with Gretchen and Greg.
Oh, wow!
Look at this. Oh!
Did you see that?
Oh! Oh...
GRETCHEN:
We stopped
at the mud volcanoes for a dip.
We had a good time.
( laughing )
COLLEEN:
We walked out of the woods
like, you know,
Lord of the Flies,
and, uh, I think the others
were quite interested
in our discovery
so we took a group field trip.
What is wrong
with you people?
Oh, my God!
GERVASE:
It was a great feeling.
It's just like a nice little
celebration for everybody.
You get together,
just get dirty,
and have a little fun--
have a couple of laughs.
COLLEEN:
Whose leg is...?
Now we really don't
want to be voted off.
JENNA:
But it's also just to get away
from the daily grind here.
I mean, we're going to be here
39 days.
You got to keep yourself happy.
RUDY:
I seen Dirk
reading his bible today.
I didn't know
he brought a bible.
"For out of the heart
come evil thoughts:
"Murder, adultery,
sexual immorality, theft,
false testimony, slander."
DIRK:
I just need that quiet time,
and especially
a lot of that quiet time
includes just praying
and meditating
and praising God.
That's kind of where I feel
all my strength and energy
comes from.
My testimony is not something
I'm afraid to share,
and that's just part
of getting to know people
and at a deeper
and deeper level.
See, the Ten Commandments
was an old covenant
that the Hebrews...
that God's chosen nation--
the Israelites,
the Hebrews--
had signed with him,
but when Christ came,
he opened the door
to every human being on Earth.
SUSAN:
I can only take
so much preaching.
I went to church,
I put my time in.
I believe in God and all that,
but to constantly
everything always come back
on to "Jesus, Jesus"...
yeah, Dirk's about
driving me wild with that.
It's getting even prettier
and prettier.
Well, thank you.
STACEY:
I think Dirk has
a little crush on Kelly.
He doesn't have
a chance in hell.
Stacey came up to me,
"Yeah, I think he likes you."
I was just, like, "oh, great,"
you know?
I-I didn't come out here
for that, you know?
We don't need that.
DIRK:
Kelly's got
a serious boyfriend,
and unless she tells me
otherwise,
that's a line
I'm not going to cross.
I love you.
But we're--
it's a platonic type of love.
I think he's really
sexually frustrated.
I've gone 23 years
without sex.
I think you guys
can go seven weeks.
SUSAN:
I went a year one time.
Oh, my God!
SUSAN:
You should
try it sometime.
You might like it.
It's just funny, but...
I know
you'll like it.
No, I know I'm
going to love it.
You'll come back.
It's a gift from God.
There's no doubt, man.
I'm obviously not a virgin,
but if he, uh...
that's how he wants
to live his life, that's cool.
You don't meet too many
23-old guys who are virgins.
He's interesting,
being a virgin, 23,
and not, uh, thinking
about crossing that line
till marriage-- hoo!
He's extraordinarily religious,
and I don't know
that we'd ever be real close
because we're on such
different ends
of the spectrum religiously.
DIRK:
Rich, you know...
homosexual people tend to talk
about their homosexuality
all the time,
and it's really annoying to me.
It's seems like
you talk about sex an awful lot.
Nobody's going to tell me
what not to do
or what not to talk about.
If it's offensive
to anybody
I stop immediately.
DIRK:
Maybe that's just me,
but if he could cut that out
it'd almost be perfect
around camp.
Day seven on the island.
After Pagong's visit
to Tribal Council
both tribes are now even
at seven members.
Today we'll see what effect
losing B.B. has on Pagong
as they prepare
for their next challenge.
Both tribes will have their work
cut out for them today,
as it requires strength,
endurance,
and most importantly, teamwork.
Try to go this one alone...
you'll never make it to shore.
Yes!
It's underwater.
"Lucky for you there's
not much to do
"to prepare for
the next big race.
"Just hold on tight,
use all your might
and stay down till
you're blue in the face."
Oh, we're going
to go diving.
Hold your breath.
"Gasping for air,
weight you can't bear,
"before you're done
you may quit,
"the fish you desire
are yours to acquire
if you're the first
to the sand spit."
Yeah, though, it's got
to be underwater,
holding your breath,
getting something
and getting somewhere.
Okay.
Come on, Seal.
Who could do that?
Well, that's what it is.
You know you're diving
for something.
Something underwater,
I'm thinking.
Yeah.
It's underwater today.
Cool.
Either lifting something
from the bottom
or carrying it
underwater,
or a distant swim
underwater
or something.
GERVASE:
The thing is this:
everybody knew coming in
water wasn't my thing--
swimming wasn't my thing,
and my team
knew it from the beginning,
so when we get into any kind
of swimming situation,
if it's actual swimming,
we're going to be struggling.
You know, they have
to compensate for me.
But that's what a team does.
JEFF:
Hey, guys.
ALL:
Hey!
Tagi, you, you saw
they're missing a member.
B.B. got voted off last night.
Today's challenge
is a reward challenge.
You won't be playing
for immunity today.
That'll happen later.
Today's challenge strictly
for a reward
that includes a fishing spear.
Here's the game...
it is a team game.
Big emphasis on the tribe.
What you're going to do is
you're going to swim out
to the inner tubes
out in the water.
Directly below the inner tube
on either side
is a sunken treasure chest.
Get that chest back here
up on your platform.
The game is over when one tribe
has their chest here
and every member
has a hand on the chest.
The only rule is
you can't dive down
to get the chest
until everybody is out there
with a hand on the inner tube.
So the race really starts here.
The quicker everybody
gets out there
the quicker you can dive down
and start to move it.
Anything not clear?
No?
Survivors, ready?
Ready.
Go!
Go! Here we go!
We're going down.
I think you're...
I can't get
ahold of it.
Everybody...
Get your hand up.
( indistinct chatter )
( all talking at once )
...two, three.
Yeah.u okay?
( all talking )
Got it?
I got it.
Come on! Come on!
Stay with us, here...
Hell, yeah.
Our beach now, baby.
That's right, baby.
( shouting )
Put your hands on it!
Tagi!
Whoo!
Way to go.
Bring it in, guys,
bring it in.
Nice job.
Man, way to get
it done, Rudy.
...than I imagined
it would be.
By the time you get
out, you're so...
Good work, guys.
JEFF:
All right, here's the deal.
The key, Mr. Hatch,
if you'd like,
to grab right there.
Yeah, Rich,
go get it, baby.
Underneath..
( indistinct chatter )
( tribe cheering )
Look at all
that booty!
Oh, money, money.
See you tomorrow.
( tribal yell )
RICHARD:
Yesterday's competition
was great.
That was the, uh, pulling
the treasure up from the water,
dragging it in and getting
a mask and snorkel.
Oh, baby, that made me
feel good.
I wanted that mask and snorkel
from day one...
to go get, uh, fish.
SEAN:
Rich, he overestimates himself
sometimes,
and we were kind of thinking
that he wasn't going
to catch anything.
When you snorkel down there,
there's nothing
to even stab at.
We have a good pole.
I have my Superpole.
Uh, which is, you know,
it works--
in a Gilligan's Island
sort of sense.
We got some maggots,
we got the Superpole 2000
and we got the persistence
of Dirk and me.
We can't lose.
Feeling good today,
buddy.
We got to come back
with fish tonight.
If somebody gets a fish
on a spear
I'll be seriously impressed.
So will I. Let's see
if he can do it.
Well, Rich is confident, man.
I appreciate...
If I was a little
fish and saw Rich swimming out,
I wouldn't be
sticking around long.
Big gay man
with a spear
coming right at me.
Oh, it's a ray.
I don't know if
it's an angel ray
or a sting ray.
RICHARD:
This is a good moment for me,
'cause I knew people
were thinking
I was just full of caca.
And it was just...
you know, one of those things
that I've been
talking about fishing,
talking about what I've
been doing all my life...
We're supposed
to eat that thing?
I will.
Just to make note
who got the first fish.
It's not a fish;
it's a ray.
Oh! Oh!
You suck.
I'm coming back
in a second
with a fish.
I actually think Sean
was kind of sad
that I beat him.
All right.
Another ray, huh?
Now you got two.
Do we want another ray?
We don't know
if they taste good
or if they're edible.
Sean said, "Get something
that looks like a fish."
This is a fish.
Look at that,
doesn't that look delicious?
No more rays.
Catch a fish.
If I see a fish,
I'll get a fish.
But if I get rays,
I'm going to get rays.
There are seven people to feed.
I don't know
if they taste good.
I'm not sure I'm
following the logic.
I mean, you're sitting here
Right..
For what?
I see a fish or something
that looks like a fish--
I mean, I'll eat whatever.
Finally, when I came up
with a third one
they said,
"Good job, good job."
Good work.
SEAN:
He pulled through.
He showed his true colors.
He does know how to spear fish.
He got us a couple of,
uh, manta rays or whatever
the hell they were.
We got fish.
No way! No way!
( screams )
Watch the spear.
Hey, baby.
Oh, hell, yeah.
We're eating dinner.
RICHARD:
My position with the tribe--
it's probably going to increase
as a result of this.
I talk about the things
that I'm capable of doing
and this might give them that
"Oh, maybe some of what
he's saying is true."
They're, uh, pretty,
pretty damn tasty.
I recommend
keep catching those...
they appear to be
slow, slow, slow.
Or you know how
to catch them.
RICHARD:
Thank you.
You need to keep me
and I'll provide you
with the fish you need.
SEAN:
I don't what I'd do without
the gay perspective anyway.
( laughs )
I don't see it at all.
We heard a rumor
that the other team
caught a fish with their spear.
The mask--
that was definitely the key
to them starting to get fish.
And that does worry me
a little bit
'cause they're going to be
eating some protein.
I would definitely rather
have fish than rat, but...
now it doesn't matter--
either/or now.
JENNA:
Ho, I'm so ready to eat rat.
I want to gut 'em, bone 'em,
and then we'll have, like,
some little rat meat
in with the rice
that we're eating.
That would be delicious.
I'm not sure
what a rat might taste like.
Nobody's said anything to me
about what it could taste like.
GERVASE:
Anytime anybody can hit one
over the head, we're hitting
them over the head, too.
Gretchen hit one
the other night--
last night--
with the soup spoon.
GREG:
This is not
an easy sport.
Oh, no.
( laughing ):
That's me!
The principle of the trap:
This noose is wrapped around
the inside of this area here.
The bait's in there
and it's getting tugged out
by the rat...
and the noose goes tight.
JOEL:
So here's our plan
with the rats.
We're going to
chop the head off
take the guts out,
take the skin off,
cut the feet off,
and pull the skin
off that way...
throw a few minnows in there,
surf and turf;
minnows and rats.
( laughing ):
All right!
I'm telling you guys
we're not going
to want to go home.
We're set.
Bring 'em on, baby.
Bring 'em on.
GREG:
Rats aren't bad.
Rats are rats.
Questions of edibility
only have to do
with your perceptions.
GERVASE:
Smells good.
Oh, yeah. We're stylin'.
Want some?
RAMONA:
Uh, what does
it taste like?
I'm not sure.
Rat?
Tastes like rat.
Almost like chicken,
a little bit.
Use your imagination.
Am I using a lot
of imagination?
Don't smell it.
Don't smell it?
No.
I'm concerned
that it'll be a bit gamy.
We won't have quite the gravy
we're looking for,
which would really be helpful.
Uh, when cooking rats
I would imagine the sauce
is of the utmost importance.
As poor as we get in the ghetto,
we don't ever eat the rats.
Ever.
Well, you guys
are missing something.
( laughing )
( groans )
Here.
All right.
( clears throat )
Gervase?
What do you think?
You having a
problem there?
We gots to kill
some more rats tonight.
( laughing with Joel )
It's on,
till the break of dawn,
like hot buttered popcorn!
Oh, yeah.
We's about the grub.
Joel, can you pass the rat?
Please?
Why you hogging
the rat, Joel?
Now everybody's taking my rat.
They're really, really good.
GERVASE:
There's plenty of food
on the island.
You won't starve
with all these rats.
There's tons of them
and they're everywhere, so...
there's definitely stuff
to eat out here.
I think people
would just rather eat
some fish instead, that's all.
We've got a clue.
RICHARD:
Cool.
"Next challenge,
choose smallest member. Stop.
"The lighter, the better. Stop.
"An emergency
has come up. Stop.
"Build sturdy, maneuverable
structure. Stop.
Tribe's fate may depend on it.
Stop."
That would be Kelly.
We probably have to carry her,
or something, somewhere--
a race.
Through the woods.
Right, right.
RICHARD:
Today's immunity challenge day
so we're building a, uh...
stretcher.
Got to be a strong one.
We don't know for what
but, uh...
obviously, it's a competition
that's going to determine
who kicks somebody out tonight.
RICHARD:
We got our mission,
Rudy.
Looks like we got to build
a stretcher.
Bamboo... bamboo...
chicken wire in here,
a brace here and
a brace there.
All right, set it
up right there.
Looks like
the head's rusty.
SUSAN:
It's important to keep
winning these games because
for one, you win the immunity.
You don't have to go
through worrying
about kicking somebody
off your team.
STACEY:
In general,
we're a really tight group.
We all have
our individual strengths
and we're pulling together,
it's just, if we could
get Rudy out of here
I think we'd be even stronger.
It's going to
have to be rope,
not that little
stuff we got.
No, we got three rolls
of the rope, Rudy.
It's hanging there.
Why don't you
just tie the rope?
( indistinct chatter )
How do you feel,
Kell?
I feel secure.
Lookin' good!
Go, baby!
Baby!
World's record!
( whooping )
"Isl "Stop!egram.
"Stop!challenge:
"Stop!e the smallest member.
"The lighter
"Stop!tter.
"Stop.ergency has come up.
"Build sturdy,
"Stop!erable stretcher.
"Tribe's fate
may depend on it.
Stop."
Yeah!
Right now, I am collecting stuff
to build a, um... stretcher.
For what, we don't know--
to carry our lightest member
and whatever else,
and through something
or over something.
I don't know.
We have some idea.
It's going to involve
the stretcher
and an evacuation--
an emergency-type thing.
We got to win, guys.
We're feeling
a little bit defensive,
but we're also feeling
like we can do it.
We can beat them
'cause we got a light person
and a strong team
pulling her.
It's not going
to be the most
comfortable ride
she's ever had.
Everybody ready?
Great!
Whoo!
Stop. Stop!
Good job!
Good job.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to Larai Larai Beach.
Another immunity challenge.
You guys got a note
asking to build a stretcher.
You were also asked
to pick one member.
An hour ago,
we took those two people
and placed them in a secret
location in the jungle.
This is an immunity challenge.
You know what that means,
but let me spell it out:
The losers are going
to the Tribal Council
where you have to vote off
another member.
All right, for the scenario,
I just need one leader
from each team
to come up here.
I'll take that immunity idol.
That's fair game again.
For today's scenario
imagine there's
been a plane wreck--
this plane right here.
On that plane was one
of your tribe members.
The good news is they're okay.
They had a parachute on.
The bad news is they are stuck
up in this jungle,
hanging from a tree.
Your job is to take
your stretcher,
get up here to where they are
and get them back down.
They are equal distance
from the beach
so everything is fair.
Once you get back down here
it's a sprint from here
all the way down
to our first aid tent.
You have to have all six people
with one hand on the stretcher.
You guys ready?
Survivors ready?
This is for immunity. Go!
Go, go, go!
( screaming ):
Help!
( Colleen screaming )
( cawing )
I'm right here!
You're so close!
( Pagong man cawing )
Colleen, where are you at?
( Colleen screaming )
( cawing )
Here, here! Get me down!
All right, you guys.
We so have this one.
All I can doulders.
is take this down...
You got it?
Almost.
No! you loose?
I need to go up more.
You got it?
Yeah.
Are you loose? Let's go.
Tagi, come on and help me!
I'm dying up here!
Come on, you guys!
All right.
Rich, I need you
up here!
Here we go.
I'm here.
Quick, get underneath her!
Stand up tall!
Good! She's down!
You got to get me.
Got her.
Get it off.
You guys have to carry me.
Let's go.
Take it.
You got the flag?
Yeah.
If it gets in
the way, drop it.
We got her,
we got her.
Keep going, guys.
We got this one.
Hold onto me.
Let's go! Go!
Go! Go!
Come on!
Wait! No!
( all shouting )
Come on!
COLLEEN:
You guys, we so won this!
Lift it!
JEFF:
There it is.
Nice job, guys.
( Colleen whooping )
JEFF:
Tagi, Tribal
Council tonight.
I know that's going to
be a tough decision
who you guys are
going to vote off.
You got the afternoon
to think about it,
and I'll see you at
the council tonight.
...all over
my back.
SUSAN:
We just got to get some fish
to keep our strength up.
Yeah.
I don't want to
do this tonight.
This is the worst one.
Yo, guys, the good news
about winning:
we have a little victory walk
planned for you.
I don't know if you've been
to Bird Island yet--
it is beautiful--
and there awaits, hanging
in the tree like Colleen,
your immunity idol.
( singing in native language )
( singing continues )
MAN:
Yeah, we got a walk-on tonight.
STACEY:
Since we lost
the challenge today
we go back to the council
tonight-- fun, fun.
Well, having lost the challenge,
we've got to vote
somebody out again.
That's what happens every time
we lose an immunity challenge.
( whistling )
KELLY:
I don't think it's going
to get any easier.
You know,
every time we go there
it's just going
to suck even more.
STACEY:
We haven't been
in this council in six days
and in those six days
we've all gotten
to know each other pretty well,
and I feel bad
'cause I know they're all,
you know, as scared
about being, you know,
voted off as I am.
I thought it was a done deal
that Rudy would be the next one
off, but it could be me.
I don't know.
It's either going to be me
or Stacey, you know,
that get voted off.
I think the younger people
are going to band together.
They're going to get rid of me
then they got
to cutthroat each other.
I'm going to vote Stacey out
at the council tonight
'cause I don't like her
and I never will.
SUSAN:
I told Stacey
I was going to vote for Rudy.
But I was thinking about
voting for her
'cause she was the weakest.
I got to think of the team;
that's what I'm here for.
RICHARD:
I've kind of prioritized people
based on who's contributing,
I think,
and can contribute most
to the competitions.
I even wanted
to talk with the group
about who we were voting for
and let's, you know,
before we even go, know,
so we could talk
with the people, but...
boy, did that not fly.
( thunderclap )
KELLY:
I don't think anybody's
out here to make friends.
I'm not out here
to make friends.
People that you're forming
alliances with now,
and the people that
you're getting along with now,
are the people
that are going to have
to turn around and vote you,
but somebody's got to go.
So, it's just the way it goes.
( thunderclap )
( gong ringing )
Go ahead and place your torches
in their slots behind you.
Take a seat.
I thought about
you earlier;
making the long
walk from your camp
to the middle of the jungle,
to Tribal Council
on what has been
one of the weirdest weather days
we've had so far.
20 minutes ago,
it was as hot
as it's ever been
and now we have
as big a storm
as we've seen.
Going to try a couple of things
differently tonight.
One is this conch shell--
the whole idea being
to see if we can get
to a little
more truth.
You ought to be
able to feel safe,
to say things here
that maybe you can't
say back at camp.
So, is there anybody here that
has something on their mind?
Have at it,
Richard.
Keep me. I'm
getting the fish.
( laughs )
I'm bringing in the fish;
don't vote me out.
JEFF:
Fair enough.
Sean, you and
Dirk went out,
tried to catch fish
for a few days.
Went out again today.
Went out
again today.
Do you feel, even though
you're putting forth the effort,
do you feel a bit threatened
by the fact that
when it comes
to assessing people's worth
Richard did deliver
and you haven't
been able to
catch any fish,
or is that just
one aspect?
No, I don't think so
right now, at this point,
but I think that Richard
catching fish
is great for the group,
and I'm pretty comfortable
with my position.
I'm somewhat entertaining,
sometimes.
I make people laugh,
and I'm keeping people healthy
and, uh, so I'm comfortable
with my role--
fishless or fishworthy.
Susan, you've been
quiet tonight.
What are you thinking right now?
I'm thinking right now that,
um, the elimination...
the way we vote is
because of the... competition--
it's like Rich getting fish
for the group.
That's not coming
into foreplay yet
'cause we're not starving
to death yet.
Maybe by day 20, we'll be, like,
yeah, he can catch fish,
he's staying
around,
you know, but, uh...
All right, it's raining too hard
to put you guys through this
any longer.
Anybody want to
say anything at all
in this downpour?
Stacey, the
floor is yours.
Yeah, you guys,
I daresay I was happy
to eat the bugs
that kept us out of here
last time,
and the games coming up are
my real strong point, so...
JEFF:
All right, guys.
You got to
survive the vote
to keep going on.
So, Sean, start us off.
It's going to be a downpour,
buddy. Write clearly.
I'm voting for Stacey.
Um, nothing personal.
I just feel that we need
as much athleticism
and brute force
in this competition.
I love her to death
and this is no reflection
on the type of person she is.
Rudy.
I'll make this quick, guys.
I'll tally the votes.
Once the votes
are tallied
the decision
is final
and the person
voted off
will need to
leave the island
immediately.
The good news is
you'll soon be drier.
With that, I will, uh...
read the names.
First vote...
"Stacey."
Next vote, fading,
"Rudy."
"Stacey."
That's two
votes for Rudy,
two votes
for Stacey.
"Stacey."
That's four
votes, Stacey.
That's a majority.
We don't need to
read the last one.
STACEY:
All right,
you switched your vote.
JEFF:
You need to bring
me your torch
if you would, please.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Well, the weather
has spoken
and the tribe
has spoken.
Okay.
It's time for you to go.
Yeah.way?
Good-bye..
As for you guys,
I don't want to send
you back out in that.
You're welcome
to stay here tonight,
or until it stops raining...
as dry as you can,
and, uh, I'll see you
at some point tomorrow.
( thunder rumbling )
( singing in native language )
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next week on Survivor:
Last night was the worst night
I've ever slept.
I don't want to sleep
in that anymore.
I'm going in the woods.
I had this vision.
I thought I'd build
myself a bowling alley.
We don't need a bowling alley.
RICHARD:
I know what the resolution
to the conflict would be,
but I'm planning something
different
and it's a little sneaky.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
They kicked off
their bug-eating hero
instead of their
food-stealing
stumbling,
ornery old Navy Seal.
Probably the guys said, "Well,
we need to vote a woman off
"'cause we need
physical strength,
and, you know, who do we think
is the least productive?"
And that would be me.
And yet I was much more
productive than the four guys.