NARRATOR: Last week
on "Survivor", Rich
woke up with a tribal
council hangover.
I got bombarded
at the council.
a little alliance tried to
attack Richie on my birthday.
NARRATOR: So he decided to fight
back by catching fewer fish.
And I'm like,
you backstabbers.
Colleen and Gervase said first
you want him out of here,
and then you're
all over the food.
Ugh.
NARRATOR: But Sue did some
backstabbing on her own.
I never trusted Rich.
He's a snake!
NARRATOR: And cracks
appeared in the alliance.
Making with Rich is
kind of like making
a deal with the devil.
NARRATOR: But it was Rich
who burned the competition.
Yeah!
NARRATOR: And won
the big prize--
immunity.
Unable to vote for
Rich at the council,
Sue and Kelly stuck
with the alliance
and sent Gervase packing.
Gervase.
NARRATOR: Only six remain.
Who will be voted off tonight?
[theme music]
I just woke up.
I'm wet, so I guess
it rained last night,
but I slept through it.
Today is the 31st day, I think.
All I know is, this is the
ninth day till the end.
People were kind of
miserable this morning.
Because I was one
of the miserable.
I mean, every day
is a little tough
because we don't have a lot
to do, and we're low energy.
I think Rich has gotten
really, really weak and really
crabby, and really hungry.
And Sean, also.
I gotta try to put on some
weight before I go home.
Everyone's telling
me I look ugly.
The food I miss but not
as much as my parents.
The hardest part for
me about being here
is that I miss my family.
And like I've reiterated 1,000
times over, I'm no mama's boy,
but I really like
to see my family.
They mean an enormous
amount to me.
When you think of their
smiles and their hugs
and stuff like that, I just
can't wait to see them.
KELLY: Colleen's legs
are pretty beat up.
She's gotten some
pretty bad gashes,
and she has some sores
up higher on her legs
that she doesn't
know how she got.
COLLEEN: My legs
are bothering me.
I mean, I would
be lying if I said
my legs aren't bothering me.
They hurt a lot.
I have all these.
And then I have these new ones.
I can't sleep because
they itch so bad.
So I get a scar, and
then I itch it off,
and it's like a
never ending cycle.
And they're going to be like
this for the next three years,
you know?
Bugs live in them.
I mean, it's awful.
It's so awful.
I am feeling like I've
been here for 59,000 days.
The past five days
have been the longest
five days of my entire life.
I miss my old team.
I miss my old beach.
You know?
I am the last sole survivor
of the Pagong Tribe.
I am a dying breed.
Pagong is picked off one by one.
That's obvious.
Now I'm very confused at
where alliances stand,
and I think they're confused
at where alliances stand.
I follow all this.
I'm going to get all of
what's happened up to here.
COLLEEN: Rich and
Sue are promising
one thing to Sean, promising
another thing to Kelly.
Sue and Kelly are promising
one thing to Rich, promising
another thing to Sean.
And then Rudy just sits back
and watches it all happen.
RICHARD: It seems
like Kelly might
be flip flopping and planning
strategies at our expense.
And that just ticked
Sue off to no end.
Kelly's trying to stay in
the alliance at this time,
but she's trying to make herself
look good to the other team
in case it comes down to the
end and she's going to be
one of the last two standing.
Because she will be like,
oh, I didn't align with them,
I didn't align with them.
And we're like this
time, no, baby doll.
You're not going to look good.
I'm here to play the game.
I'm going to play that game.
I don't give a rat's ass
what people think about me.
I don't have to prove
anything to anybody.
I know who I am.
So who cares?
That's what's so interesting
about this, because I'm getting
to see the breakdown of
the Tagi alliance, which
is really funny.
Everybody is very concerned
about the money at this point.
Like Sean was saying
for a one in six
chance of winning $1
million, and nobody's
going to throw that away.
They'll be gunning for
us if they're not already.
I think they are.
Comes to the point where we
have to turncoat a little bit,
be a little more strategic, a
little more self preservative.
It's a serious contest.
There's a lot of money
at stake, and I better
start treating it that way.
No one's here just
to make friends
and shake hands and
have relationships
for the rest of the time.
Where's Kelly and Sue?
They went for food.
They went for wood that way?
That way.
So now it's you
and me to the end.
Period.
I've given you my word.
You know, if I
got along the way
by somebody that gave me their
word, I'd do something to them.
You're the only one
I've been able to trust
from the beginning.
And you can right to the end.
Right.
COLLEEN: It's definitely
what happens when you
put a big chunk of
cheese in a maze
and let all the mice go at it,
you know, and see who eats who
and who scrambles on top of who.
And I don't want to
be any part of it.
It's not a fun game now.
What does it say?
Survivor trivia.
It's not your muscles
you'll strain.
For tomorrow's event,
you'll work out your brain.
We got a clue last night,
and it says you can use
your brain, not your muscles.
Which is good news.
Not that my brain's any
good, but I'd rather
use that than my muscles.
Because the muscles hurt now.
I suck at trivia,
but I love it.
Because you know, I'm
real slow at the buzzer.
But you know what I
was thinking before I
went to bed last night?
I was like, it's going to
be just like a game show.
This is going to be so cool.
Then I was like, wait a minute.
We're on a game show!
My friends, today
decadence speaks.
Oh, we're liking this.
We've taken the visa
and created a really cool
night tonight for one of you.
Oh.
Come on!
One night on a yacht.
That yacht.
But you got your TV
and your stereo, sure.
You got your luxury
dinner with your waiter.
Oh my god.
Fresh sheets, beautiful
bed, and a hot, hot shower.
Pretty simple.
You guys are going to
start at the end, ABC
all the way through.
True, false, or multiple choice.
You're going to start
on the blue squares.
And as you answer
questions correctly,
you'll move forward through
the different colors.
Now, if you're the last
one left on a color
that others have already moved
beyond, you're out of the game.
First one on the mat gets
the night on the yacht.
Let's do it.
Take your spots.
For a night on the
yacht, here we go.
True or false.
Pound for pound,
insects are a better
source of protein than beef?
Stare straight ahead.
Everybody take a step forward.
You are right.
Almost 80% of an insect
is good for protein.
All right.
What must be done
to water collected
from inside green bamboo
before it's safe to drink?
A, nothing.
B, it must be strain.
C, it must be boiled.
Or D, it must be distilled.
Nothing is right.
If it's inside the
bamboo, it's OK.
Richard, you had it.
Rudy, Colleen, step forward.
Kelly.
What?
You're out, buddy.
Man!
If you do not have water,
you should A, not sleep.
B, not eat.
C, stay on your feet.
Or D, stay active.
Everybody move a step forward.
Not eat, because digestion
removes even more fluid.
Susan, I'm sorry.
Yeah, just saying--
yeah, I'm out of here.
Last one.
Join your pal, Kelly.
True or false.
If you eat a poisonous mushroom
and survive the first 24 hours,
you have a 90% chance
of full recovery.
Richard, move into the lead.
That is false.
Some mushrooms, in
fact, you recover
from in the first 24 hours and
then die 2 to 10 days later.
Oh, baby!
You can still see the
boat through the fog, Jeff.
What is the longest
venomous snake in the world?
A, King Cobra.
B, giant sea snake.
C, reticulate python.
Or D, Kinabalu pit viper.
Sean, move up with Richard.
It was A, the King Cobra.
True or false, the
dangerous female Black Widow
spider is identified
by a blue hourglass
pattern on her abdomen?
What's the right
answer, Richard?
Red.
Red, false.
You and Sean move forward.
We have a showdown.
No!
Colleen, Rudy, sorry, guys.
Which of the following?
Can you drink to kill
intestinal parasites?
A, distilled water.
B, mango juice.
C, kerosene.
D, ginger ale.
Both ready?
Yeah.
Richard, you really
wanted that, didn't you?
Did I lose it?
Sean, congratulations.
C, kerosene.
Oh, I thought
that would kill you.
Good job.
Sean, congratulations.
That yacht right
there is all yours.
One night, hot shower, hot
towels, and everything else
we talked about.
Way to go, man.
Good job, Seany.
Oh, Sean, here's one
more thing to consider.
One other person may
be able to join you
for breakfast on that yacht.
So I'll let that sort
of ruminate in your head
as you contemplate
this whole thing.
Otherwise, it's going
to be a great night.
Party on the boat!
Woo!
SEAN: OK, yesterday
I won a challenge,
an island trivia contest.
The reward to the challenge
was, lucky for me,
is a night on this
luxurious yacht.
I understand there's
going to be food,
I hope dessert, a warm shower,
television, maybe a newspaper.
But hopefully I get to
bring some company with me.
I'm allowed one person.
I owe Kelly a dinner,
so she's coming with me.
I really like Sean.
I probably talked a
lot of trash about Sean
because he's neurotic
and talks a lot,
but he's really a good guy.
If he does get to
bring one person,
he said he's going
to bring me, so I'm
a little stoked up about that.
I might get to go spend
a night on a yacht,
which would be cool.
Because if I could
spend a night on a yacht
and shower and eat some
food, I'd be good to go
for another seven days.
This is an
ungodly type of rain
that we're not used
to in the States.
You know, I've seen some heavy
rain pours in New York City,
but this is heavy, heavy rain.
I mean, serious rain.
This is really horrible.
Survival of the fittest.
Who can stand in an umbrella
in the rain the longest.
That piece of
crap parachute thing
has been the most
waterproof thing
we've had on this whole island.
So a lot of people have been
crowding up underneath that.
Today is raining.
Last night it was raining.
And I think tomorrow it
will probably be raining.
This is definitely
the worst day.
MAN: Definitely the
worst day by far.
And it's really bad,
because it's probably
going to be like this tomorrow.
As far as rain, I think
it was a big deterrent
to a lot of people.
It really kind of ate at them.
Oh my God.
I don't know if I
want to [inaudible]..
Ornery, tired, hungry, cold.
Put it this way.
It beats driving a semis
through Chicago at 4 o'clock
on a Friday summer afternoon.
Thank God for the sun.
So the sky's really
clear, and everybody's
drying out and warming up.
Good stuff.
Rainbow.
Pretty.
Check out the
rainbow you're on.
Wow.
That's great!
What's happening, Jeff?
Well, you know,
I wish I was coming
here to say that everybody
was going on the yacht.
So do we.
Let's go.
See you, buddy.
Have fun.
See you in the morning.
See you guys tomorrow.
Have fun.
See you guys.
Bye, guys.
Sorry you're not coming.
Sean finally leaves to go
off to his yacht excursion.
And then he hollers
out, hey, I can
invite somebody for breakfast.
I can invite
someone for breakfast.
Who wants it?
Take her?
Kelly, do you want
that to be your meal?
Sean, it's your decision.
Don't pawn it off on me.
Yeah, Sean, get some
balls and make a decision!
Richie, scrambled eggs.
See you in the morning, Hatch!
Sean makes up his mind
and he invites Rich.
Come on, Rich.
You need a boost!
Sean kept saying how
he was going to take me.
And then last
minute, he said, Oh.
Oh, Rich, you like eggs
for breakfast, don't you?
OK.
Me and you, Rich.
I'll take you.
The guy's dumb.
He's so dumb.
Is he not?
Sean is probably
eating lots of food.
I wonder if he's got pizza.
You know, we're all hungry, and
tired, and dirty, and bored.
He'll probably shave and bathe.
He might get a massage.
I don't think he's
ever had a massage.
Oh, that feels so good, Jane.
I just hope the
poor kid doesn't
make a fool out of himself.
Does my ass look
as boney as it feels?
[slap]
The captain, he's not going
to be steering all night.
He's going to go to sleep.
I just wanted to
introduce him to you.
Just for, you know.
But this guy just
really wanted to say hi.
And you know, he's
familiar with the show.
He's certainly familiar with you
and everything that's going on.
OK.
So come on in
and take the oar.
Whatever.
Hi.
Captain.
Hey, Dad!
Oh, my god!
Holy Toledo!
How are you?
How's my boy.
Oh, Pops, I love you.
I love you, too, son.
Oh my God!
You look fantastic.
I can't believe you
got my father here.
Oh my God.
Dad, you made my
whole adventure.
I cannot tell you
how much more this
is worth than $1 million to me.
I can't even tell you.
I thought the
reward, ample enough,
to spend a night on a yacht,
get a massage, shower, shave.
And to see my father there,
I mean, it was just a dream
come true.
--so, so much.
Are you kidding me?
You can't beat him.
He's got a heart twice
as big as this body.
It's twice as big as your body.
It's the truth, son.
I'd walk on nails, coals.
I don't care.
Anything.
Yeah, me too.
Me too.
I don't know why
our bond's so strong.
It is.
But we got a very strong bond.
You're the best.
The dad is looped.
Yeah, yeah.
Have my wine.
I am so happy right now.
[inaudible]
I just wish Sean would just
get a backbone sometimes.
It irks me, the way he
tried to put it on me.
Like, I'm going to bring you,
but you can pass it on to Rich
if you want to.
Like he didn't want
to be the [muted]..
he didn't want to want to
have to make the decision that
was his to make.
It's dawn, and I'm
looking at the yacht.
Sean's probably still
sleeping, but it
won't be long before they
come get me for breakfast.
Rich, get your
skinny ass down here.
My skinny ass?
Hey.
Hey, tell Sean he's
in big trouble!
Tell Sean he's got to deal with
Wigglesworth when he gets back!
Wow.
That'll spoil his whole morning.
Hey, she's hungry!
It's not even the food
that pissed me off.
That's a point of it.
It's the point that
he's been going on,
and on, and on, about how--
How he screwed you
out of of a meal.
How he screwed
me and he owes me.
And then when it comes
down to it, he can't even--
Where's Sean at?
Hey!
There he is.
Hey, Captain.
I take it that's the captain.
That's his captain, all right.
Did you have a good night?
I thought you needed
something to pull
you out of your doldrums.
This is going to do it, buddy.
Up we go.
Seany.
Thanks for the shower
and everything.
My pleasure.
Welcome to breakfast.
Meet the captain.
Also known as Jim
Kenniff, my father.
Oh.
He is not!
Yeah.
Holy Moses!
It was good.
It was enjoyable.
I just kept eating while
they talked and answered
questions as I chewed.
It was rocking pretty hard.
Yeah, plus you get an
hour boat right here,
and then we tossed back
two bottles of wine.
Recognized how much
we loved each other.
You know, all that
good father-son stuff.
Oh my God.
Just dump it out.
This is all your guys' food.
What is this?
Cinnamon rolls?
Yes, it is.
Thanks for picking me, Sean.
Cheers, cheers.
Nice to meet you, Dad.
Yeah, I'm a little--
No worries.
Six more days of rice.
I might even skip the last
day of eating altogether.
Just to not eat rice.
Mexican food.
Chips.
Chips and salsa.
Then guacamole.
Enchiladas.
Sean is seeing that he's
in a little bit of trouble,
and that he should probably
have Rich out there,
because Richard's going
to make sure that I get
voted off tonight and not him.
Maybe somewhere
he's thinking that.
He's smart if he's
thinking that.
I like that.
Good job, Sean.
I can't figure it out, why
he switched at the last minute.
But all them ladies
are pissed off at him.
Richard better
bring a haul back.
Literally.
I have so much to tell you guys.
I am definitely getting--
oh, you all right?
You all right?
I got caught in the rope.
Six out of six votes tonight.
Unless you came
back with something,
we don't care if you're back.
This is my father, guys.
Meet Mr. Kenniff.
Come on over here.
What?
Sean's father.
Shut up.
What?
So much to tell you guys.
Yeah, we can tell him how
dumb you were not to take
Kelly with when you owed her.
You know, he kept
some food for everybody.
Pay back your debts before--
Hi.
He bought-- he
got food for us.
Colleen, Sue.
Hi.
Hi, Sue.
Kelly.
I thought about it.
He's provided food
for us 50 times.
When Sean's dad first
came, to tell you the truth,
I almost cried.
Because I started thinking
about my mom, and I got so--
a lot.
You know, Sean just
gets all the breaks.
But you know, it was good.
It was good.
I felt happy for him,
and he is the family kid.
You know, so it
was good for him.
It was nice to have a new
face around and stuff.
Never caught a fish.
Super pole 2000.
And nothing has been
happening in the news.
I know you're all
wondering what's happening.
There's nothing going on.
It's boring, eh?
What's the stock
market's been doing?
Staying steady or going up?
Oh, no.
We had some bad days there.
Did you?
400 and something points
on the NASDAQ went down.
What's it down to?
What's the NASDAQ down?
It didn't bounce up.
I haven't-- the last
few days, I don't know.
Actually, for him
to come and visit
the camp was sort of cool,
but he didn't know anything!
So that war over in Russia
sort of mellowed out?
What?
They had the one there.
Chechen.
Oh, the Chechen?
- Yeah
- I don't know.
I don't know.
We're like, what's
going on in the world?
He didn't know none of that.
What about the college playoffs?
Who won?
- I don't--
Oh, yeah.
Wait a minute.
No.
Yeah?
Who the hell won?
See, I'm not really
a sports fan.
Oh, he's just like Sean.
He's just lovable but doof.
I'm gonna say
goodbye to my father.
Tired?
Pleasure to meet you, Jim.
Same here.
I've got something
for all of you.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, geez.
Oh, boy.
Like Santa Claus.
Daddy Claus.
What's this stuff?
This is [inaudible].
Real funny, Dad.
Guess what this is.
He needs clothes, see?
What about everybody else?
Then right when
he goes to leave
this afternoon, about an
hour an a half, hour ago,
he has this gray bag.
And in it there's a care
package for each one of us.
Rich.
Thank you.
Somebody's grateful.
Kelly.
So nice.
Oh, look at this!
So in it we each got a little
something from one of our loved
ones from back home.
Thank you!
I don't know.
You know that is, don't you?
Even though we are
apart, just remember,
you are always in my heart.
We all got thrown
a bone, which was
amazingly wonderfully great.
Because now I feel like I can
do this for six more days.
And I definitely will.
I'm on a sugar high right now.
More than I have
been in a month.
So I feel like I can
do anything right now.
Thank you so much!
Oh, my pleasure.
Unbelievable.
I love this.
This is so nice.
Thanks for being the
bearer of good treasure.
Great meeting you all.
Love youse all.
Pop, I love you.
My son, my son, my son.
Tell my mother I love her.
Oh, I will.
Oh.
I'll tell everybody.
Tell them I'll see them soon.
Bye, Pop!
Thank you!
Plenty of food.
I don't care.
I'm drifting away for a while,
just kind of going home.
And it's phenomenal.
God, I can't wait
to get out of here.
Sean's father came back with a
bag filled with things for each
of us from particular people.
And this made it from
the most wonderful woman
on the planet, Valerie.
She just printed out
the email that she was--
was having with her husband,
who's another incredible man,
close friend of mine.
And it just takes me back
to my real world life,
and has my brain
engaged and rejuvenated,
and out of these 16
whoever they are people,
and into who I am, and just
knowing what's going on
and that it's back there, and
what I'm about to experience
when I go back.
You know, I can last the other
whatever's left, seven days,
six days.
Hey, guys.
Hi, Jeff.
This challenge
is for immunity.
Whoever wins gets the
talisman, cannot be voted off
at tonight's tribal council.
It's all about will, this game.
You're going to be
standing on planks.
Over a period of time, I'm
going to remove certain planks
till we get down to one plank.
Last person standing gets the
talisman and is safe tonight.
This game can take 15 minutes.
It can take 15 hours.
You will decide that.
Only rule-- you
can't touch anybody.
But you can taunt all you want.
All right, let's
go out and do it.
Survivors ready?
Ready.
Go.
OK!
Got it.
Did you think somebody
would be gone yet?
No.
You now why I'm cutting.
I'm pulling this board.
81 bottles of
beer on the wall.
81 bottles of beer!
You take one down,
you pass it around,
80 bottles of beer on the wall.
Say, 80 bottles of beer.
You take one down, pass it
around and 79 bottles of beer
on the wall!
It's moving.
Damn it, Rich.
79 bottles of
beer on the wall.
79 bottles of beer.
You take one down,
pass it around,
78 bottles of beer on the wall.
78 bottles of beer on the
wall, 78 bottles of beer.
Woo!
77 bottles of
beer on the wall.
You just gave up?
No.
You just dropped?
I dropped.
He couldn't take it anymore.
77 bottles of beer!
I slipped.
65 bottles of beer!
You take one down,
pass it around,
64 bottles of beer on the wall!
Out of the way, buddy.
I'm sorry to leave
you without my music.
Please.
See you onshore.
Amen to that.
Hey, Rich.
So it's ironic that
Colleen is even trying.
Because she thinks
she's dead tonight.
I asked her today.
I said, Colleen,
what makes you happy?
And she said, you know,
Rich, irony makes me happy.
So I think it's
ironic that she's
trying to stay on the
board, and she's not even
in danger of getting voted off.
Kelly, on the other hand,
has no idea that she's
leaving this evening.
But it's still--
I'll bet Sean gets two
votes from the girls.
Yeah, Sean may get
votes from Colleen.
Colleen and--
And maybe Kelly,
just to throw a vote.
Yeah, because Kelly's
trying to look as if she's
not part of the voting bloc.
Like, oh.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, go!
Go!
Look at her.
She's almost gone.
But she's miss dancer.
So maybe she's got balance.
Well, he's cut one side.
Now he;s cut the other,
and they're all wobbling.
Look at the wobble.
And the play by play.
As we look at Sue, she's got the
arms up level across the side,
but Kelly, holy Moses, she
looks like she's going.
Back and forth.
Oh, no.
Colleen looking rather
stable, although determined,
really trying to hang
on, thinking she's
about to be ejected
this evening.
Sean just-- there he goes.
Sean falls off the board,
and it is down to 3.
Look at them.
Oh, Sue.
It's Kelly and Colleen.
Holy Moses.
OK, Sue, so if Kelly wins
immunity, what happened?
Sean or Colleen?
I'm thinking Sean.
Are you thinking
Sean before Colleen?
What are you thinking?
I'll go with
what you guys say.
What do you think?
I'm feeling, you
know, aw, Sean, Sean.
But we've been Aw, Sean,
Seaning, you know--
SUE: I think it was [inaudible].
OK.
Rudy says Sean.
So If Kelly hangs in there,
Sean is out of here tonight.
So we got to watch, because
it's down to the wire.
Oh my God.
You aren't cold after being
out there for so long?
I got to dry off
before I put clothes on.
No, no.
I'm fatter than you, remember?
RICHARD: There Kelly.
RUDY: They're both gone.
They're both waving.
RICHARD: I think when one
wobbles, the other wobbles.
Oh, God, Colleen.
This is good.
This is really good.
Am I getting
voted off if I fall?
Not by me
By the rest?
I don't know, honey.
I don't know.
I'm guessing yes.
Kelly, you got immunity.
Colleen moved.
Woo!
Well done.
Very well done.
Because this is so--
all you guys were
doing out there
was saying "my feet are
dying, my feet are dying,"
what are you wearing to
tribal council tonight?
Shoes?
OK, insoles from Dr. Scholz.
Hopefully they'll give you
a little padding on that.
Good job, Kelly!
Thank you.
This stupid alliance thing.
I don't even care
about that anymore.
You know, I say I'm not.
I'm not in it anymore.
I'm voting my conscience.
And you know, I want
to be true to myself
and who I am and
keep my dignity.
Who cares?
Kelly, she was a double
agent, so to speak.
You know, talking to
the Pagong people,
really trying to
get in with them,
and then relaying everything
we said to her teammates.
The Pagong people
fortunately picked up on that.
Because they all
came to me in unison.
They said, they think
Kelly is up to no good.
And so it was very
plastic, very see-through.
And even her biggest
advocate on this island, Sue,
saw right through that.
I'm voting strategically.
So are they.
And they still think I'm
in the stupid alliance.
Because if I told them I didn't
want to be, they'd vote me off.
So I'm trying to
save my own ass.
So how bold and
wonderful is that?
Me and Kelly, I thought we
had a real friendship going.
I really did.
But when I turn around
and see somebody
starting to dig a
knife into my backside,
it just really pisses me off.
I don't care what
I say to people.
I don't care if I'm nice
to anybody at camp anymore.
I do not give a [muted].
And it feels so good.
It's great.
I love it.
Welcome to tribal council 11.
We're going to bring
in our jury now.
It consists of Greg,
Jenna, and as of last week,
Gervase, who was the
last person voted off.
Two of you will make
it to the final vote.
The other four will
join these three,
and we'll decide who
gets the $1 million.
So let's talk about
what's gone on
since the last tribal council.
A busy, busy time, a lot of
it hovering around you, Sean.
One decision, though,
you had to make
was right as we left heading out
to the yacht, I said you know
what, why don't you invite
somebody for breakfast?
Correct.
Put you in a tough spot.
Very tough spot.
You had to pick somebody.
Absolutely.
So what made you change
your mind at the last minute?
Rich provides food.
You know, the women that I
was blessed for on the island.
But let's not forget the
fact that you said, "Kelly,
all right, I'm
going to take you,
but you can give it to
Rich, so I don't know.
It's in your hands."
- Let me tell you.
I'll tell you why.
And she knows it.
You tried to
pawn it off on me.
Rich also gave us
tons, tons of food.
He goes out every day
fishing for four hours,
comes back with something in
his basket 9 out of 10 times.
Which is really
great for the tribe.
But you didn't say that.
SEAN: But that's
what I'm thinking.
So.
A day later.
SEAN: No, what do you
mean, a day later?
Not at all.
He was in my thoughts when
I mentioned breakfast.
He really wanted to go on
that ship during the contest.
I factored all that into
it, and I said, tell me,
who wants to come?
And I yelled from
the ship, and I
just made an instant decision.
If it was the wrong one and
it gets me a boat from Kelly,
I'm sorry, Kelly.
But either way.
It's not about the food, Sean.
Yeah.
It's the fact that the whole
day before you were saying,
oh, I'm going to take you.
I mean, you don't
owe me anything.
It's not about that.
So?
It's just the fact that
you were just saying--
I felt obliged.
that's all.
OK, Richard.
Yeah.
JEFF: Two tribal councils
ago, you got three votes.
Yeah.
The only thing that saved
you was the now infamous
alphabet system, which
cast a vote for Jenna
was the swing vote.
I mean, other people
voted for Jenna,
but it was that swing
vote that was based
on the alphabet that saved you.
Looked that way, yeah.
It seems like at
this point, if I'm just
looking at it on
paper, you would be
in a very precarious situation.
I could be going home tonight.
Absolutely.
How about you, Colleen?
Last tribal council you said,
I'm either going tonight, Jeff,
or I'm going the
next tribal council.
I mean, I'm feeling--
I'm feeling-- I'm
feeling like I'm going.
Yeah, I mean, I'm the last.
I'm the last of my kind here.
I'm the last Pagong.
So yeah.
JEFF: What's your gut on
how nasty it's going to get?
Hmm, what's my gut on how
nasty it's going to get?
It's going to get pretty nasty.
There's a lot of stuff going on.
OK, it's time to vote.
Rich.
Oh.
Why are you going tonight?
Because you screwed up.
It wasn't your turn.
And you were supposed to stay.
So you're actually being
sacrificed, even though you
were supposed to stay.
But good night.
I can't vote for myself,
so I got to vote for Sean.
Because same reason
as last week, really.
He knows.
"24/7" is all I have to say.
I'm voting for Colleen.
Even though she calls
me a putz all the time,
I know we're good friends,
and I like her a lot.
She's a cool girl.
So I'm voting.
I'm changing her
name to Cooleen.
And she's really cool, though.
I enjoyed her company.
And I'll probably see her
next vote in the jury.
Across from you now are
10 torches representing
the first 10 people voted off.
Tonight, we will add one
more staff to that group.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are tallied,
the decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the island immediately.
They will return, however,
to the next tribal council
as the fourth member
of our final jury.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Sean.
Colleen.
Sean.
Two votes for Colleen,
two votes for Sean.
Three votes Colleen.
Colleen, you need to
bring me your torch.
(WHISPERING) Be nice
to each other, OK?
I swear, I'm watching you.
Bye.
OK.
Play fair, OK?
JEFF: Colleen, the
tribe has spoken.
Step forward.
Well, I heard Colleen's last
words, "play fair, be nice."
She's a wonderful person.
JEFF: You guys can grab your
torches and head back to camp.
NARRATOR: Next
week on "Survivor."
This is the most
conniving bunch of people
I have ever met in my life.
There's not an honest
one in the bunch.
Things are falling apart
here at Rattanna Beach.
Oh, and you told him you
weren't aligned with us.
Because colleen told me that.
That's bull.
Well, I don't give a [muted].
Because I trust her
more than I trust you.
I had a lot of fun,
and the past week
was actually the hardest
part of the whole thing.
I'm excited now
for the next step.
I want to sit in the jury box.
If I came into this
game on Tagi's team,
I think I could have won.
I'm just going to
say it, you know.
I mean, no harm in saying it
now after I've been kicked off
and I didn't win.
But really, I think
I could have won.