JEFF PROBST:
From this tiny,
Malaysian fishing village,
these 16 Americans are
beginning the adventure
of a lifetime.
They have volunteered
to be marooned for 39 days
on mysterious Borneo.
This is their story.
This is Survivor.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
Are we getting two of these?
Where's that box?
JEFF:
You are witnessing 16 Americans
begin an adventure
that will forever change
their lives.
They've been given two minutes
to salvage whatever they can
off this boat.
Their destination:
this island right here,
a beautiful,
but dangerous jungle
in the middle
in the South China Sea.
Who's got oars?!
Oh, we got our lifejackets.
For the next 39 days,
they'll be marooned,
left to fend for themselves,
no creature comforts.
They are wiping the slate clean.
Grab it!
16 strangers forced
to band together
to carve out a new existence,
totally accountable
for their actions.
They must learn to adapt,
or they're voted off.
In the end,
only one will remain
and will leave the island
with $1 million in cash
as their reward.
Go, go, go!
39 days, 16 people,
one survivor.
Grab it!
Hey, behind you!
Get off the raft!
Get off the other side!
The rod, Sean!
Listen up!
Grab your backpacks!
Put them on!
Go! Let's do it!
Whoo!
Here we go!
The 16 contestants have been
separated into two tribes
named after the beaches
where they will live.
The Tagi Tribe,
who will always wear orange,
consists of: Sean Kenniff
a neurologist from Long Island;
Kelly Wiglesworth,
a river guide from Las Vegas;
Rudy Boesch, a retired Navy
SEAL from Virginia;
Sonja Christopher,
a 63-year-old cancer survivor
from San Francisco;
Richard Hatch, a corporate
communications consultant
from Rhode Island;
Susan Hawk, a truck driver
from Wisconsin;
Dirk Been, a young dairy
farmer, also from Wisconsin,
and Stacey Stillman,
a litigation attorney
from San Francisco.
The Pagong Tribe,
who will always wear yellow,
consists of:
Gervase Peterson,
a YMCA basketball coach
from Philadelphia;
Colleen Haskell, an advertising
student from Miami;
B.B. Andersen, a real estate
developer from Kansas city;
Ramona Gray,
a biochemist from New Jersey;
Gretchen Cordy, a preschool
teacher from Tennessee;
Greg Buis, a recent Ivy League
graduate from Colorado;
Jenna Lewis, a single mother
and full-time student
from new Hampshire,
and Joel Klug, a health club
consultant from Little Rock.
( shouting orders
to each other )
Hard to imagine
that just four hours ago,
this group met
for the first time
in a small fishing village
on the coast of Borneo.
Their minds racing
with questions,
wondering, "Can I do this?"
This is more than just a test
of survival skills.
It's also a test
of social skills.
Here, it's the impressions
you make on the other castaways
that determines your fate.
Under the rules, one tribe
must visit Tribal Council
every three days
with a single purpose:
vote one of their own members
off the island.
To win, you must survive
the island,
survive the vote,
and, ultimately,
survive each other.
Whoo!
I'm giving you
a degree--
a university
honorary degree.
Whoo!
Damn, when you
guys get up,
now the whole
thing goes...
Whoa! Watch out!
Here we go.
We got a great view
of Snake Island!
Get to work.
We got oars.
We got buckets.
We're set for months.
Hey, who knows, we could make
a mud house with it.
You know,
that could be like rebar.
RUDY:
Paddling over, we had two
or three of those boxes
in the water,
dragging them behind the raft
and that is dumb.
I said,
"Let's get them boxes aboard.
It'll be a lot easier."
You know,
"That's deadweight you got."
KELLY:
He was yelling at everybody
"Let's lose the box!
Cut it loose now!"
He may be 72 years old
and an ex-Navy SEAL,
but that doesn't mean
that this is his world.
RICHARD:
Rudy, Sean, Stacey, Sue,
can we take 15 minutes
and just talk before
we do anything?
Sure.
Can we piss first?
Just a suggestion.
Should we take
a break?
No, keep paddling!
One break at a time!
One water break at a time.
We want to get closer
to the island
before we turn up.
I'll distill you
all the water you want,
just get me
to the island.
You guys, we are so close.
Keep going,
we're there.
( retching noise )
You all right?
We're almost there,
Roe, hang in.
Okay.
Got it going
right over here.
Where'd he point?f us.
Right there.
Straight up there.
Whoo!
And we're all here.
Let's go.
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
This is what I was
talking about!
Ramona, how you
doing, honey?
RAMONA:
I don't like being on the water
all that much.
So, I mean, the whole motion
like this,
and we're rowing,
and we have like 100 pounds
of stuff on the raft,
I just, I started heaving.
Good job.
RAMONA:
I'm used to being in a lab
with my lab coat on,
in the air-conditioning.
But this is, like, outdoors,
24-7,
and you're exerting energy,
like, almost all of that time.
Oh, my God.
This is just Day One.
Should we, uh, you know,
talk for a little bit,
or should we start moving
stuff up?
Hey, let's discuss some things,
man.
Let's figure some things out.
Here's what we
plan on doing.
High tide is that
line right there,
see that line?
Yeah, uh-huh.
So it shouldn't
come up to here.
And this piece of
bamboo back here,
we can lay it from up here,
over to there,
and that'll be the beginning
of our shelter.
Actually, before
we build a shelter,
just knock that
whole branch off.
No, I mean, this
is an awesome spot.
I'm just saying...
What's the first thing
we need to do?
We need a latrine.
Okay, so we don't need
fire tonight?
That's an option.
We got enough water
to make it tonight.
You guys, I think first
thing we ought to do
is talk about how
we're going to do
whatever
we're going to do--
talk about the process.
Listen, listen.
Let me give you
a rough quick.
The camp will be
right there.
We'll clear these leaves off.
That's a flat piece of ground.
The latrine will be down there.
The wind's hitting me
in the back right now.
SEAN:
So, we're saying
we need a latrine
and a clear place
to sleep, is that all?
Food.
And if we need
more...
Let's check the box,
before we make
any decisions.
Let's see what we got.
There might be a
blowtorch in there.
We need a bathroom.
Are you guys
all done talking?
Huh?
I don't know.
I'm done.
I'm going to open
up a box.
I'm looking
for Fritos.
DIRK:
Rich, um, I appreciate
what he's trying to do
as far as bring the team
together and stuff,
'cause that's one thing
that needs to happen.
I think he's got some good
skills in that area.
And, unfortunately,
people like that annoy me.
I'm just thinking,
I think we're off
to a bad start.
Why, 'cause
we're not talking?
Yeah.
Sometimes, though,
Richard, um,
you kind of got
to do things
and talk
as you go along,
and sometimes things
can't be that planned out.
I agree with you.
The problem with having
no conversation whatsoever,
or lots of people talking
about different things
is that nobody's working
toward a particular goal.
Not the silly
little stuff about,
oh, who's going
to sleep where?
What are we
going to do?
But why are we here?
And what's the point?
And if we don't...
Oh, I figured that out
before I come here.
And you haven't?
And I have for me,
but we haven't for us.
And for the next
seven ejections,
21 days, we have
to function together,
or we fail.
What do you think
we're doing now?
Not functioning
together at all.
I'm a redneck, and I don't know
corporate world at all,
and corporate world
ain't gonna work out here
in the bush.
No, I'm not talking
corporate world.
I'm talking
creating a team.
I thought we were doing good.
But, see, creating a team
is actually putting
all of our hands together...
Not hands, all of us knowing
what we're doing.
Yeah, the hand thing,
yeah, but that's...
Action, man. Action, Richard.
Action.
Well, you don't want
to act ahead.
RICHARD:
I'm good to go survivalwise.
Peoplewise, it'll be
a little more challenging.
But I've got the million dollar
check written already.
I mean, I'm the winner.
And it's that kind of cocky
attitude that makes people
really hate your guts.
So that's the kind of thing,
I've really got to keep, uh...
under wraps.
But, uh, it's just,
how do I get there from here?
What's that?
Whoa! Look at this, folks.
If this is kerosene,
and we didn't take
one of those lamps...
We can make torches
and stuff out of twine.
We could twine all
the rafts together.
JOEL:
What is that?
Biscuits.
Yeah, it's
definitely biscuits,
'cause we got corn...
Well, look, we
got a frying pan.
Oh, we are so set.
Look, I'm shaking it.
Can anyone hear
the biscuits?
Oh, ho, we got
a team flag.
Whoo-hoo!
If that's our latrine,
I say we
dig a hole,
put this here,
knock a board
out of the bottom,
then we can keep
moving it across.
Let's plug the hole.
SEAN:
Let's sit down and talk
about what the hell
we're going to do.
RICHARD:
Can I help?
When I asked earlier
about having a conversation,
that's what I was talking about,
and I really can help
with how we can do this.
We wanted to see...
You guys, we came over here
to talk.
We just want
to see what we...
RICHARD:
What happens when
people get together is
if they aren't all
headed in the same direction,
toward a particular goal,
then things that individuals do
kind of get in the way
of the whole team, and I think
it's really, really important
that what we decide
be decided as a group.
So, if you hear somebody
saying something
and you're all aggravated
with them, stop,
don't try to make your point
and try and help them
make theirs.
So, for example,
you know, Sean,
what do you think
a main point
of what I'm trying
to say now is?
I didn't listen to a word you...
I've been daydreaming, thinking,
"What am I going to eat?"
Well, you'll
begin to figure
that out...
All right, we
got a stick up.
Well, as long as they can
hit the middle of this hole,
we're all set here.
Put it right like this.
This is perfect.
Hey, we found a water map!
You got it?
We got a water map.
B.B.:
"Enter jungle here."
"Walk 375 paces
along..."
Oh, we start here.
We go back
to the other stream down there
and then we get
the water here.
B.B.:
Here's where we are right here.
We have to go
across the stream.
We go across one stream...
two streams,
three streams.
Two streams,
All right.
All right,
we're ready to roll.
All right.
You all right?
Okay, is this the path?
Well, it said
"newly cut path."
It looks
newly cut, but...
"trail washes out."
Oh, the trail
washes out.
Oh, wa...?
No?
B.B.:
Why don't you stay there
for a minute?
Let me walk
and keep you
in sight...
Okay.
...to see if I see...
Anything?
...anything
that resembles anything.
( sighs )
Do you see anything?
Huh?
Look here.
I mean, come here
and look at it.
Okay, ready?
Oh, thank you,
Jesus.
Christ!
Yeah.
There we are.
Go ahead.
All right.
Way to go, B.B.
Don't let me drop
sweat in there.
Okay, it's almost full.
You know, we could
never do this,
but you know what
thought crossed my mind?
What?
As long as you
and I always know
where the water is
and we got control
of the water map,
no one else will
be able to vote
you or I out.
We're not giving up
the secret...
We're not giving
up the secret.
...of the water supply.
That's right!
( all chuckling )
And your wife
is how old now?
B.B.:
My wife?
Right now?
Yeah.
She's 45.
Wow. And how old are you?
64.
Oh, you better go.
You are a stud.
He's a stud!
His name's Viagra.
Viagra. That's his nickname.
Dang!
You know, you got to do
what you got to do, right?
Somebody has to do
the dirty work.
If we don't keep some humor...
we'll go mad.
Good night, y'all.
Good night.
Stretch out.
RUDY:
The hardest part
is hanging around
with all these young kids.
I don't even know
what MTV means, you know?
And I'm used to being
in the military
and one guy stands up,
he gives an order
and there's no back talk.
You know, like yesterday,
everybody's trying
to run the show
and if they'd let
one person do it,
we'd be much better off.
But trying to keep them all
shut up is hard.
If they listen to me,
they'd all have haircuts
and everything else, you know.
We'd be in formation
in the morning
and all that kind of stuff,
but they're not
going to do that.
I got to fit in, not them.
You know, there's more of them
than there is of me.
Hey, you got
a pierced nipple, eh?
Yeah. I got the ol'
pierced nipple thing.
How did that feel?
Pretty edgy for
a doctor, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I thought I was making it
with the hair
and then this morning,
when I ran my hand through it
and felt these couple
of golf ball-sized knots in it,
I'm like, no, they got
to come out now.
SONJA:
I was doing something.
I don't even remember
how I did it.
Betadine won't hurt it,
yeah, so we'll give it
a little shot of Betadine.
I think these are
the only sponges we have,
so I'm just going
to keep reusing them.
Okay.
SONJA:
I've been thrashing around
like I'm 35,
instead of acting my age,
but we have a doctor
in our tribe-- uh, Sean--
and he did a wonderful job
of bandaging me up.
I think one of the problems
with aging
is the thinning of the skin,
darn it,
and so I think I'm maybe
getting a little more banged up
than some of the younger ones.
My aim leaves something
to be desired,
but we're getting there.
Try this?
Well, I don't know.
This is heavier.
It might be
sharper, though.
Think so?
I'm wondering 'cause
that's so damn hard.
Well, that's off.
That ain't gonna work.
Here's a, uh, a therapist's
version of "Bye, Bye, Blues,"
if I can remember it.
♪ Bye-bye blues ♪
♪ Thanks to Prozac ♪
♪ Give me Paxil ♪
♪ Bells ring, birds sing ♪
♪ Sun is shining,
no more whining ♪
♪ I live through,
ba, da, da-da ♪
♪ Life is hell, but I'm swell ♪
♪ Bye-bye, bye blues. ♪
Yeah, that's awesome, awesome.
Fantastic.
RICHARD:
Well, the fish traps
were hanging from the boat
that we were coming over here,
and when we were
tossed into the sea on the raft
and we could take whatever
we could get our hands on,
we grabbed
three or four fish traps
and a bunch of rat traps,
and so we stuck the rat traps
out the first night
and boom-- we got a rat
in each of them.
Bait. I want bait!
Give me bait!
I think he's just going
to cut its head off.
Ew!
Oh, God!
Oh, no way!
( laughing )
Remember that knife.
We're not using it
for anything else.
Oh, dude!
RAMONA:
I didn't sleep at all.
I mean,
we-we closed our eyes.
We kept hearing noises
and, like, clicking sounds,
and we're, like, okay.
Um, what's his name...
WOMAN::
Joel.
Uh, Joel woke up,
a rat was, like, in his ear.
JOEL:
I heard something squeaking
in my ear.
A rat was trying
to get on the raft,
or get near us
or get at something.
I mean, everything was moving.
B.B.:
We're just going
along the beach here
and just identifying
whatever we can use
for the shelter, the roof.
And I'm a little irritated
that none of the others
are down here to help
carry stuff, but that's okay.
We need...
we need five more of these.
B.B....
He's a character, man.
I don't think he likes me much.
Just these.
No, no,
you don't understand.
I got to have this thought out
and positioned right.
GRETCHEN:
He's right, Joel,
or it's not going
to fit the frame.
Joel, trust me.
I'm not the
one bitching.
I mean, I'm fine.
Hey, don't be
talking to me
about monkey
business.
I can't sleep,
so I'm usually up.
...this being the width.
B.B.:
We got a lot of lazy people
if you want to know the truth.
You can't do it all yourself.
You know, I asked Colleen
to straighten this out for me
and here it is.
That's the only thing
she had to do today.
You can't have lazy people.
GRETCHEN:
He had been out there,
you know, all morning long
and, um... you know,
it was hot.
GRETCHEN:
B.B., I thought we said
that this was a time of day,
we were going to be
out of the sun.
Well, but for some of us...
some of the people,
it's been all day that way.
Right,
it's your turn.
You tell me
what you're doing here
and I'll help you.
You hold it up
and I'll do it quick.
I promise you,
I'll do it quick.
That, you know,
that's the right
way to do it,
but we won't have
near enough line
to build the roof
and do that
if we do all this,
in all fairness.
Anyway, don't
stop now, but...
I think we'll have plenty,
and I'm going to roll that up
for you, too.
We can't, like,
get burned out, though.
I'm not burned out.
I know,
but you will be
if you spend all day
out in the sun.
No, I never
get burned out.
You don't know me.
I don't know you,
but I know human beings.
Okay.
I like working
as a hobby.
Honest to God,
how about 15 minutes though?
Sit down for 15 minutes.
Why? Yeah, but,
I want to get...
I want to get this thing
stabilized so at least...
But, B.B., look...
Let me just explain.
I want to get this stabilized so
then people can come in here...
You know the light cords
you got?
And we can tie
these things down,
but until I get this bounce
out of this...
I want to... I'm going to put
a support there
in the middle here
and right there.
'Cause if not, we
got to take bounce
out of this.
I just think we have
plenty of time.
I thought we were going
to try to stay competitive,
and if you work all day
and you're burnt
at the end of the day,
we're not going to be
competitive.
Take a break, and if it bounces
a little tonight,
then we'll fix it tomorrow.
I'm going to keep working,
sweetheart.
You're going to get
burned out.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
You already are.
B.B.:
Oh, my.
You're doing fine.
Too much paper.
Yeah.
Bifocals work?
Bifocals worked.
You the man, B.
No, she took
my bifocals...
We're both the man.
And made it happen.
B.B.:
And the fire started
because I had bought
a set of glasses with me.
I was going to do it
and Gretchen said,
"Why don't I do it?
I know how to do it, too."
So, I said, "Great."
Nice, guys. You guys
split up and everything.
Good work.
B.B.:
And she took my glasses
and started the fire.
You did well, Gretch.
If we get fire,
it means we're going to have
a hot meal in our stomach
which is going to bring up
team morale.
That first meal
might be rat soup,
which I'm, like,
looking forward to very much
because there's nothing wrong
with a rat.
All a rat is, is a squirrel
without a fuzzy tail.
Let's just work with this.
Okay.
I'm thinking,
if we could work with this,
we're getting
a ton of smoke.
Start that
If we get a piece of bamboo,
someone sits here and holds
the bamboo right here
With the kindling
in it.he kindling in it.
You know what I'm saying?
Here we go.
Come on, Dirk.
Go big.
This isn't
going to catch.
Well, you want
to just keep trying?
Why don't we try
and make the bough?
MAN:
Go...!
Come on!
We're getting there!
All right! Okay!
Don't stop!
There was smoke.
We lost it.
Yeah. of smoke.
Don't you guys...
Cool!
How much more do we need?
I don't know.
How much more?
That'll do it.
You in, Rich?
Here we go.
Work it, Rich.
Yeah.
What?
You guys get ready
to take his spot.
Take a break, man.
We made a lot smoke but no fire.
I think it would have been nice
if we had fire,
but we're not going
to catch fish
unless we have fire to cook it
and I think that
if we had fire,
we could have spent
a lot of time sitting
around the bonfire
at night maybe singing songs.
We have a ukulele, you know,
and that didn't happen
and I wish it did.
Throughout their time
on the island,
the tribes will compete
in a series of challenges.
They'll receive messages
notifying them
of these competitions
at their tree mail.
Today's challenge is
for both reward,
in the form of 50 waterproof
matches, and immunity.
Win immunity, you stay
on the island a few days longer.
Lose, face Tribal Council,
where you must vote one member
off the island.
Ooh.
A map to fire.
It's got to be.
"Cold food, dark camp,
"just a reminder
of your first night.
It looks so easy
in the book." Yes.
"Why is it so hard to light?
"Tonight your tribe
will carry the torch.
"One tribe takes
home the flame.
The other gives
someone the boot."
Whoa!
Whoa.
I guess they're
combining the reward
and immunity challenge
this time.
That's the competition
is taking home the flame,
but what's the competition?
We've got no freakin' idea.
Welcome, tribes,
to your first challenge.
Congratulations
on your first night
on the island--
should be very proud.
I know both of
you guys have food.
You found some
fresh water
and I think, Pagong,
you guys had fire.
( cheers )
Right on.
A lot of work to get fire.
Yeah.
Yeah, it takes
a lot of work.
With the threat of rain
always a constant,
even if you guys
did have fire,
you're certainly not back there
tending to them now.
50 waterproof matches
should certainly make that
a lot easier.
It's one of the things
you're playing
for tonight-- the
other is this:
I want everybody to touch this,
get a good feel of this.
This is your life
on the island.
This is the immunity idol.
Oh. Ah.
Win this,
you stay on
the island a
few days longer.
Lose...
you face
tomorrow's Tribal Council,
where one of
you will be
the first person
voted off the island.
Big enough stakes?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, here's what we're doing.
There are two rafts
about 150 feet
out in the water.
Your job is to get your raft
back to the beach.
Along the way, a series
of torches both in the water
and on the land.
First team to light
all their torches
and their side of the fire
spirit wins immunity.
Here are the rules:
Each tribe member
has to have one
hand on the raft
at all times--
at all times.
Nobody can
swim ahead.
Nobody can fall behind.
The other rule: you have
to light every torch.
Don't put me in the position
of having to make
a judgment call.
I don't want to.
There's too much at stake.
Clear?
ALL:
Clear.
All right,
swim out to your rafts.
Wait for my signal.
Okay, Sue, listen up.
You're going to hold this.
How's that feel
for you carrying?
JEFF:
Here we go!
A storm is approaching!
Waterproof matches
and immunity at stake!
Go!
Here we go!
You got to lift.
Come on, team!
Here we go!
Light it! Light it!
Dry run it.
Go, go, go!
Slow it down.
Go!
Come on, y'all.
Come on.go.
Do not wait for me.
( all yelling )
No, no, no!
Go. Go. We got it.
Good job.
Go!
( all yelling )
Throw it!
Go! Here we go! Come on!
To the flag!
Calm down.
Pick it up.
Here comes the wave.
Let's go.
Move it! Move it!
Move it!
Move it, move
it, move it!
Move it, move it,
move it!
Make sure
you get it.
Let's go!
Here we go!
Stop!
Come on, team!
We're doing good.
Three!
Come on!
Go!
Seven!till there!
We're doing it,
we're doing it,
we're doing it.
We're still there.
Come on.
Come on!
We're still there!
We're still
there!
We win!
Going back!
It's lit! It's lit!
No, keep it there.
We got it!
Yay!
Yeah, baby!
( screaming )
Yes!
JEFF:
Guys, great
competition.
Really close.
Pagong, you get
fire in the form
of 50 waterproof
matches.
( team yelling )
And more
importantly...
immunity from tomorrow's
Tribal Council.
You'll stay on the
island a few more days.
This is happening
every time!
Every time, this
is happening!
Every time!
JEFF:
Tagi.
That's why
we're winning.
We're going to stay...
Our island!
Tagi.
Nice competition.
You know the drill.
You have a date
with me tomorrow
for the Tribal Council,
where one of
you will be
the first person
voted off.
You guys seen Dirk?
Where the hell did he go?
Oh, he goes...
He brought his bible with him?
Yeah.
I think he's
pretty religious.
He was telling me he was
a youth minister or something.
( reading quietly )
Rain's coming.
Again?
That's all right.
I could always use
a wash.
RUDY:
Before we got
on the island here,
I formed opinions
about people,
but I changed my mind
just on that trip in.
Rich, for one.
I mean, this guy is...
He's strong.
He's smart.
The guy surprises me.
You know, he's fat, but he's...
( chuckling ):
he's good.
You can lay it
over those.
RICHARD:
I like Rudy.
I'm not bothered
by his straightforwardness
at all.
I don't think
it's even a problem.
I-I like it that he's saying
"Hey, do this,"
or, "Hey, do that,"
but people are thinking of that
as very direct and arrogant.
That's the word I'm hearing,
and I'm thinking to myself
"Well, they think he's arrogant;
Oh, my God, I'm out of here!"
( thuds )
Oh, my gosh.
What do we got?
The good news is
we'll be having fire tonight.
The bad news is
one of us won't be
here to enjoy it.
We got Tribal Council tonight.
"Pack your bags,
get ready to go,
which one it will be,
the world will soon know."
KELLY:
Unfortunately, we're going
to have to vote somebody off.
There's going to be
a lot of tension
and one of us is going to leave.
Well, what time we
got to do this at?
It just said,
"Get ready to go."
Just, "Pack your bags,
get ready to go."
I can't believe
we have to pack up.
We're just getting settled.
Well, somebody's gone.
So, it's time to think
about who are they going
to vote for?
Why are they going to vote?
I've narrowed it down to four.
I'm one of them.
Well, it could mean a lot
uh, either staying
or being voted out.
You know,
last night's competition,
I really feel responsible
because I couldn't keep up
and I was dragged totally
off my feet.
I do feel that that stumble
probably cost us
the immunity challenge,
and that's a big one.
Up until, uh,
probably last night,
I never gave it
a second thought
about who I was going
to vote off
or if I got voted off,
but after last night, uh...
I thought about it then,
and I decided then.
I feel pretty secure, actually,
about the vote tonight.
Kelly and I get along
real well
and we've been talking
about strategy, and, you know,
who's not contributing
as much, and who would be best
to vote off,
and I think we-we've come
to a mutual decision
and we've talked to Sue
about it.
Stacey came up to me,
and it's, like,
she don't like Rudy
and she's, like,
"Oh, I think we're going
to vote for Rudy,"
and vote him off
'cause he's so barking."
Well, anybody's too barking
and too bossy to Stacey
because she doesn't
move her ass.
The chicks think I'm voting
for one person, and I'm not.
This is Tribal Council,
where each week
one member will be voted
off the island.
Last night,
in a crushing defeat
Tagi lost the immunity
challenge,
so, tonight, they will come here
and vote the first person off.
It all begins
with a dangerous hike
through the jungle.
With so little time
to get acquainted,
everyone is vulnerable.
Rich's talk-versus-action
approach
may be more annoying
than helpful.
Sonja's tumble
cost them dearly.
One thing's for certain:
At Tribal Council,
you are held accountable
for your actions.
There will be a vote.
Someone is going home.
I see torches.
Oh, that looks
pretty hairy.
( birds chirping )
( gong sounds )
Make our way around.
We begin
Tribal Council
with a ritual.
Behind each of you is a torch.
I'd like you to grab the torch
and approach the fire.
Go ahead and
dip your torches
in the flame
and light them.
Put them back in their
slot, and take a seat.
We do this because--
as I'm sure
you've discovered--
on the island,
fire represents life.
These torches now represent
your life, your identity
here at
Tribal Council.
The good news is
you will take these torches
with you when you leave
so you will have fire,
and you will bring them
back with you
to each Tribal Council.
Go ahead and
have a seat.
Well, leave it to me
to state the obvious,
but this is not a
place you want to be.
You tread in dangerous territory
every time you come here.
Tribal Council
is basically
where you account
for your actions
on the island.
Some of
those actions
will come back
to help you.
Some of them may come
back to haunt you,
but tonight, based
on those actions,
one of you will be
the first person
voted off the island.
So, before we
get to the vote,
let's talk about
what's been going on.
I'm curious
just about you guys getting here
and finding this place.
How was the
journey over here?
Saw two deadly snakes.
Really?
SUSAN:
Grand Canyon
mud slides...
It was great.
It was fun.
We're still starving.
We've eaten
but not really.
SONJA:
The competition
is stiffer.
we had last night was tough,
tougher than I had anticipated.
How are you holding up,
physically?
SONJA:
Well, pretty well,
you know.
I'll fight to the finish,
but, uh, I have my blisters
and whatnot,
but I'm-I'm doing okay.
What happened
after Quest for Fire?
That was a great competition--
obviously,
a lot at stake.
SONJA:
Oh, God.
We came close.
We almost got it.
SUSAN:
Aw, man, we were
dragged down two times
and we were right there.
We almost got it.
SUSAN:
There's no way.
All right, guys, well...
it's obviously a fun group.
This is not
a pleasant process...
No, not at all.
JEFF:
And I know also,
from listening
to you guys talk,
that there are
a lot of different
reasons why you're here.
Obviously, $1 million--
big motivator for anybody,
but I'm sensing
there could be
personal reasons,
different journeys
you might be on
that-that this
encompasses.
Whatever it is,
to fulfill
that agenda,
you have to survive
tonight's Tribal Council.
That's the way it's set up.
So, what we're
going to do is vote
and how it
will work is
you'll come
down here.
You'll go across
this bridge
into our voting
confessional.
Write the name of the person
you want to vote off--
large, clear letters.
Hold it up,
and speak your piece.
We can't hear you.
Fold it up, put it
in the container,
come back, and
take a seat.
Now, once the votes are tallied,
the decision is final
and you have to leave
the Tribal Council
area immediately.
It's time to vote.
You're first.
Got to remove the weakest link
in the... crew.
Stacey.
Um, tough call.
( sighs )
Subtle reasons...
I'm not sure
exactly what they are.
He's just...
He's an ornery guy...
doesn't really help that much.
For a Navy SEAL, he doesn't know
how to start fire...
and he
just criticizes everything.
I'm picking her
because I think she's the reason
we lost yesterday.
I'll miss his, uh, skills
and, um,
his speaking his mind openly.
Before I read these votes,
I just want to commend you
on the courage it's
taken to get this far.
There were a lot of
steps along the way.
Any of you could've
turned around.
Nobody did,
and in my book
that gives you bragging
rights for life.
So, with that,
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Sonja.
Sonja.
Stacey.
Rudy.
That's three
for Sonja
and three for Rudy.
The first person
voted off the island...
Sonja.
Sonja, I need you
to grab your torch
and bring
it to me.
The tribe
has spoken.
Go get 'em, you guys.
RICH:
Thanks, Sonja.
Thank you.
JEFF:
Well, to the rest
of you, I guess
a somber
congratulations.
You've survived
the Tribal Council.
You have fire.
You can head back to camp
and I will see you tomorrow
for the next challenge.
Good night.
JEFF:
Next week, on Survivor...
I've been
working my ass off
and a lot of you have been
laying on your ass watching me.
Don't give me any of that ....
RUDY:
Me and Richard got to be
pretty good friends--
not in a homosexual way,
that's for sure.
( screaming and laughing )
Swallow it, Gervase!
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Well, I think this has been,
uh, an awesome experience.
Being the first to be voted out
is a little humiliating.
On the other hand,
the team did the right thing.
They're a terrific group
of people.
They're very strong physically,
and I-I think in their shoes,
I'd probably do the same thing.