JEFF PROBST:
16 Americans forced
to abandon ship
in the middle
of the South China Sea.
Marooned for 39 days,
they must work together
to build shelter, find food
and survive the island,
but ultimately,
it is everyone for themselves.
Every third night, they will
hike deep into the jungle
to take part
in the Tribal Council
where they must vote one
of their own off the island.
In the end,
only one will remain
and will leave the island
with $1 million in cash.
Last week on Survivor:
Conflict within the tribes
continued to emerge.
You can only
take so much preaching.
Dirk's about driving me
wild with that.
When Christ came, He opened
the door to every human being.
We've all sort of
come to the conclusion
that Rudy really needs
to get out
of here-- he just criticizes
whatever we're doing.
Come into the kitchen, "Morning,
Rudy, how are you doing?"
"You're wasting
your time out there."
JEFF:
The oomph is a little gone.
I think that not eating
is a factor.
( laughs ):
We want food.
JEFF:
Tagi Tribe gained advantage
by winning a reward challenge.
I wanted that mask
and snorkel from day one
to go get fish.
We got fish.
No way. No way!
Watch the spear.
JEFF:
Pagong was forced
to look elsewhere for food.
JENNA:
I'm so ready to eat rat.
I want to gut 'em, bone 'em...
JOEL:
Surf 'n' turf. Minnows and rat.
GREG:
Rats aren't bad.
Rats are rats.
Questions of edibility only have
to do with your perceptions.
RAMONA:
Please pass the rat.
JEFF:
But Pagong rebounded by
winning the immunity challenge,
and Tagi Tribe was sent back
to Tribal Council in the middle
of a tropical storm.
STACEY:
I thought Rudy would be
the next one off,
but it could be me.
RUDY:
I'm going to vote Stacey out,
'cause I don't like her
and I never will.
JEFF:
Stacey. That's four
votes, Stacey.
It's time for you to go.
13 are left.
Who will be voted off
this week,
and who will continue
to survive?
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
( thunder rumbling )
I'm not a happy camper.
GERVASE:
It's cold, man.
It got cold and rained a lot,
and everybody got, I mean...
everybody was just wet.
RAMONA:
It was long, wet and cold.
It was the worst night
I've ever slept.
GREG:
And worse trouble
was the bugs--
the bugs love it.
Once that rain comes,
it's sand flea heaven.
GRETCHEN:
I have spent six years
at the Air Force
survival school.
You know, we learned how
to make fires and shelters.
Come on...
When we got here,
we argued over
where the shelter should be,
and everything I've always
been taught, you know,
you put it up off the beach,
you get canopy cover,
which is your first layer
of protection,
but we made this huge shelter,
which was not comfortable
and it's not practical.
It's a rain forest,
so it was going to pour
one of these times,
and it poured,
and we got soaking wet,
and I just thought,
"This is ridiculous," you know.
And also,
the gear is everywhere.
Our rice bucket's down there;
the shovel's down there;
we don't know, you know, where
the parangs are in the morning,
and... it's got to stop.
What's the reason
for that, though?
It's not up-tide-- look.
The shovel is over there
'cause we just dug...
I know, but you're done digging,
so the shovel...
We don't know if
it's done yet.
GRETCHEN:
I think I am a little
frustrated with Joel today
because Joel wants
to take over,
and that's fine,
but Joel doesn't know about...
where we're going to be
the most comfortable,
and so, you know,
after last night, I thought,
"Well, I just can't let
this go on anymore."
You want to vote me off, fine,
but we got to organize this.
I don't want to sleep
in that anymore, okay?
You can sleep on the
beach if you want to.
I don't want to sleep
on the beach anymore.
I don't want to be antisocial,
but I'm going in the woods.
Why don't we just go?
Why don't we just start?
We get to move--
it's so exciting
when you get to move
to a new place.
Oh, man, it's hot.
GRETCHEN:
If this were, right now,
each man for himself,
Greg would be the victor.
He's relaxed.
He's not fighting this.
It's not like a battle for him.
Greg's a character, man.
Hold on one second. Yeah?
Greg talks into a coconut
and thinks it's a phone.
This guy wants
to do an interview
for four or five minutes.
GREG:
The naturephone is really a way
that I kind of keep in touch
with the greater, um...
the greater spirit out here.
All right, listen, well,
uh, yeah, just hold my calls
if, uh, anybody's in this...
You get reception everywhere.
You're always incommunicado
with everything
and anyone, and, uh...
you know, it's light,
it's quick, it's easy,
and it's relatively inexpensive.
Do you have a fitting
for bamboo?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah,
as quickly as possible.
GRETCHEN:
Greg knows what he's doing--
he kind of
manipulates the group,
and I think
a lot of people don't even
realize it's going on.
I think most of the people don't
even realize it's going on,
but in his own way,
Greg's the leader.
Okay. Yeah, yeah.
Two min... Okay, bye.
Sorry about that.
Hit Greg in the head.
SEAN:
Sue, she just always keeps
working, working, working.
You know,
it just drives everybody crazy.
I mean, the guys were talking
about that today.
I wish she would slow down
for a little bit and just relax.
SUSAN:
We're getting by
on coconut and rice.
You know,
whatever we can gather,
and we're still not done
looking for tapioca or nuts.
Tapioca.
Tapioca's supposed
to have red lines.
Got to find the tapioca.
SEAN:
I had this vision,
and, uh, I thought I'd
build myself a bowling alley
right about here.
That's what I'm doing here,
slaving away.
( Susan grunts with effort )
This little...
Aw, this is all woody.
What I think I might do is,
I might take
some of those coconuts
over there--
that are lined up like that--
I might take that bamboo
over there
and make, like, a little shelf
where you can have the extra
balls hanging out up there?
No, that's a stalk.
Oh, is that...
that's those big nuts.
Sean's telling me looking
for nuts is a waste of time.
But at least you know
you can find a nut.
Sean sits there for five hours
and builds his bowling alley.
He could've been
all getting nuts or looking
for tapioca during the day.
I'm tired of feeding people
that don't do anything.
If we lose tomorrow,
I'm voting Sean off.
My parents would be so proud.
Throughout their time
on the island,
the tribes will compete
in a series of challenges.
They'll receive messages
notifying them of these
competitions at tree mail.
Today's mail
informs both tribes
about their next
reward challenge
called "Distress Signal."
Hey, you guys!
JEFF:
They'll build an S.O.S.
on their respective beaches.
A plane flying overhead
will determine whose signal
is the most creative
and parachute in
a crate full of supplies.
Both tribes
have been instructed
to send a representative
to see the creature comforts
they'll be competing for.
We've got a nice luxury
going on-- whoa!
JEFF:
Things like hammocks,
towels and pillows.
Oh, my God!
JEFF:
But Jenna and Dirk
have each requested
one additional item
be placed into the crate.
We want a spice rack,
including salt, pepper,
garlic, soy sauce...
Then you would have
a full-out competition
for that spice rack.
What would make it
worthwhile for you?
We need a
flay knife.
JEFF:
Here's the deal-- two clues
for tomorrow's challenge.
Do me a favor, though.
Don't open them
till you get back to camp.
I'll do what I can
about the reward.
Right on.ing to you.
Nice talking
All right!s.
All right. the nap.
A spice rack
is the best.
Good for you.
I wouldn't have
thought of that one.
COLLEEN:
What happened?
What did we get?
We got this.
COLLEEN:
What is it?
Okay, okay, okay.
"A store you all know
has decided to show
"some support
to the survivors here.
"The noise you hear humming
is a plane that is coming
"to drop a crate
filled with gear.
"Soft pillows of down,
hammocks off-ground,
"a bar of soap
to wash up some,
"a crisp white towel,
so you won't feel so...
Towel!
( laughing )
"...some toilet paper
to wipe off your bum.
"The gift is only won
as you work under the sun.
Remember, this challenge
matches wit."
Oh, you guys,
we so have this.
Can I tell you something else,
what the prize is?
They added,
because I finagled...
A spice rack.
JENNA:
Oh, yeah, baby.
Tomorrow morning,
a plane flies over
two hours after the sunrise.
And it has to be on our beach--
anything-- a symbol, a word,
you could spell out anything.
"Naked."
I know what
goes best.
Something really good.
One quick bonfire.
No, hell, no.
We got to do something
bigger and better!
They do one big bonfire,
one big bonfire...
Yawn.
You do the
fire but...
We got to sell it!
This is like advertising;
we're selling this spot.
Simple but... impact.
GREG:
What's creative, though,
and exciting to
see from up high?
Sex, naked people...
We're trapped on
a desert island, you know?
We're horny.
( laughing )
There's also going to be
a spice rack in there
and one phat, filthy,
stainless steel flay knife.
Yeah, something we need.
All right? So, we need,
we've got one chance.
We've got
to do this right.
Ideas?
RUDY:
Tomorrow, right?
It's gonna be daylight.
We'll make a
lot of smoke.
Smoke, a lot
of wet wood.
KELLY:
We should bring it
over by the fire.
Have the fire
blazing to all hell.
It's not about size;
it's not about fire.
Well, fire is going to help.
SEAN:
There's a little bit
of conflict of ideas
between everybody right now,
uh, regarding our next event.
SUSAN:
Are you against that?
Nobody's against it,
but we want to figure...
SUSAN:
Yeah, but two hours...
RICHARD:
There was conflict there
between Dirk and Sue
when she was trying to get going
and Dirk was saying, "No,"
and she made fun of his swagger.
Let's have a clear plan,
then let's go to work,
you know what I'm saying?
Thank you, Sue.
The ideas I didn't like
were just some of the things
that maybe were a little bit
tasteless or...
you know, and don't have
much class, you know?
I believe that class kind of
shows itself, and things like...
Condoms.
If we had
enough condoms
and they were
different-colored,
that would be so funny.
I don't know if that
has much class, you know.
You guys could put the little
orange thingies on your wieners.
That's not very creative.
That's just looking
in a bathroom stall wall.
RICHARD:
We can also use
those white
Styrofoam floats
and create a big
arrow in the water
that's, you know,
pointed right
toward the beach.
That's an idea;
that's an idea.
I don't think
we can do it together
without the things floating
all discombobulated.
Yay, Mr. Positive.
All right.
RICHARD:
An idea comes up and you
can see on people's faces
when Sean is negative about it,
and then they'll just harp on it
and make it...
want it even more.
SEAN:
I just think
that we need
to do something simple
but extravagant.
Like one thing
that we all work on.
You know, similar to, like...
like the Rose Bowl.
SEAN:
I just wish people would,
you know, see things my way,
in terms of,
I think that what they want
is something really spectacular,
and I think that we could work
through the night and build
something really spectacular
that would ensure us
getting that crate.
What's happening in my head is,
"Here's the conflict.
"Here comes
the dynamics that suck.
"Here come the people that
just shout and don't listen.
Here comes the negativity,
and here comes the crap."
You talk about
doing a float
Not a float,
or sa project.hat...
It could be
I ka big "X."ject.
You know, we build
a tremendous "X"
in the sand and
stand it up.
Did you think I was done
with my sentence?
Well, I know what the resolution
to the conflict
that exists right now
would be at home,
but I'm actually planning
something different from that
that might benefit me,
and it's a little sneaky.
( chuckling )
I think
I'm going to handle this
by beginning
to develop alliances
with some folks
to ensure that I move
into the next round.
That means we need
to clean up that beach.
JENNA:
I don't think Ramona's
pulling her weight.
I think that she really thought
she could handle this,
and now she's finding
that I don't think she...
she can as much as she thought.
Ugh.
Yesterday was bad, bad night.
The only thing
Ramona can be is herself.
I'm a mama's girl.
Well, I'm mama's
only child, so...
She has great gifts to offer.
Maybe she will be able to.
Maybe she won't.
But I can't do any more
than I can do,
and I'm not going to try
and bust my ass
and try and prove something.
Every chance she got,
she was just making it worse.
And I'll expend
extra energy.
I'll give this
one to him.
I tried to pull her to the side
and just
point certain things out to her
and try to get her
to correct that situation.
Everybody's in cliques,
and I'm, like, here.
It's all about everybody
being nice.
You don't want to be
out there kissing
everybody's ass,
you know what I mean?
Don't start withdrawing
in yourself now,
you know, like... going solo.
DIRK:
I really like our slogan--
I think it's going
to grab someone's attention.
We're giving it our best shot.
We want to win.
GERVASE:
Work-wise,
Ramona seemed today
to be, "Oh, I'll help here,
I'll help here.
I'll do this, I'll do that."
RAMONA:
I feel more like a part
of the group,
and I don't know if that's
because I'm feeling better
and therefore
I'm working more and harder,
or if it's because, like,
I've started to assert myself.
I don't know,
I guess it's a combination.
GERVASE:
Looking forward to getting
a spice rack
to flavor up the rice.
And towels. I'm the only one
who wants towels.
And pillows.
I like the pillows.
Where do you
want to cross?
Um, right here.
Here.
Yeah... yeah,
Who you talking to?!nd time.
The pilot,
the pilot of the plane.
Can you hear me?!
Yeah. I don't want to tell you
exactly what it looks like.
It's, uh...
just put it this way:
we're all very excited
to be here.
JEFF:
It's 10:11 on the island,
and aside from the ever-present
desire for more food,
both tribes have begun to
reprioritize those core items--
the things that would make life
a bit easier.
We're currently flying
above the island.
On board, one crate filled with,
among other things,
a few hammocks, several pillows,
one spice rack and one knife.
The tribe whose distress signal
is most clearly visible
from this plane gets it all.
KELLY:
Hey! Hey! Come on!
( imitating Tattoo
from Fantasy Island ):
"De plane! De plane!"
Here we come approaching Tagi.
( all chanting ):
Spice... rack...
up...
PROBST:
That's very good.
"Tagi is groggy!"
We're gong to swing over now
and take a look at Pagong.
Here it comes!
Whoo!
Save us!
GERVASE:
Come on!
Save us!
We're banking towards Pagong
right now.
We're about as close to them
as you can get.
They have a smiley face.
We're going to make
one more pass.
I'm going to confer
with the captain
and also the drop master
and see what their thoughts are.
Please! Please!
They're not going
to drop it.
MAN:
Up, two, three,
down, two three..
Right here, please.
PROBST:
I've conferred with the pilot
and the drop master,
guys that do this for a living.
We're all three in agreement:
Pagong has a great
distress signal,
but the addition of human bodies
colorfully dressed, moving,
makes Tagi's distress signal
more clear from the air.
Therefore,
Tagi is getting
the care package.
There it is.
( cheering )
That drop boy can go.
It's hard being
this good.
this stinky.
( tauntingly ):
♪ We got your
spice rack! ♪
♪ We got your spice rack! ♪
How about a big "aw"
for the other team?
Aw!
Let's go get it.
Whoo!
GRETCHEN:
All that waiting,
all that work
for nothing.
Man, I wanted garlic.
Yo, look what we found.
There we go. Let's see.
Ah! We like
it there.
Ooh!
Look at the knife!
Yeah!
That's something
to fish.
Now we're eating.
Spices.
This looks
like oregano.
What do we got in there?
Curry.
I think this is garlic.
RICHARD:
That's where
you'll always find it--
around my thigh.
You think they're bummed
about their spices?
I'll take a victory
over Jenna right now.
Groggy no more.
That's right, man.
I didn't like
the final decision
for the S.O.S. Game.
I thought it was quite silly--
a smiley face?
Give me a break.
I didn't expect us
to win anyway.
It's a little disappointing,
but it's okay.
So it's another day of rice.
I'm down.
I hate to lose.
It sucks.
But tomorrow's the one
that counts, so...
trying to look up.
KELLY:
The whole idea of an alliance
is to make sure we're all...
voting the same way.
So are we going
to stick to it?
I'm going
to stick to it.
RICHARD:
So the, um...
alliances have begun,
and I didn't even have
to do much about it.
I don't want to
vote anyone off...
I agree with Rich, I think,
about the Sean thing.
Yeah.
KELLY:
Sue and I had discussed
on our own about
getting Richard in the same vote
and us three having
the same vote.
So no matter what,
even if we never talk again,
the next vote is...?
KELLY:
Because the more people you
know that are going to vote
for somebody else,
you might as well go with that.
You might as well, you know,
keep yourself safe,
and, you know,
keep it in the majority.
We have alliances that are
happening within the group,
and you're going to have that,
just because, you know,
everybody's...
hey, there's money involved.
We really could control our fate
if we stick together.
I think what's going
to happen in the end,
there'll be alliances.
TheOh, yeah!be.
KELLY:
We really like Rudy.
Rudy's kind of crabby,
but he's a lot better
to get along with, you know,
than the two boys.
At least he's honest.
You know, he'll tell you,
you know,
"Up yours," in a second.
Sue!
What, if anything,
should be said to Rudy?
RUDY:
Somebody said that
if you want to sort of gang up
against somebody,
you ought to talk about it
to get rid of them, but, uh,
I don't agree with that,
so I'm not doing it.
I don't know
about the rest of them.
RICHARD:
It's hard to kind
of trust people
completely and thoroughly,
but I think
until the next segment,
the three of us
can work together
really well.
I trust you
coYeah.ely.
RICHARD:
I think we can trust
the three of our votes,
'cause if one of us blows up,
trustworthiness-wise,
then this whole thing's
out the window
and it's... it's a free-for-all.
The three of us
against the world.
( laughing )
This is going to be
so good.
You want a small spoon
or a big spoon?
I'll take a small one
'cause I got a big mouth.
Jenna-- she's like
this Energizer bunny
that, like, keeps going
and going
and going.
( trilling )
Pagong!
RAMONA:
Like, I haven't had
a white friend
since, like,
junior high school,
and I really can see her
being, like,
my first white friend
in a long time.
GRETCHEN:
I think Ramona's change
has to do with
she's feeling more comfortable,
she's feeling better.
She feels like
she's more part of the group,
which I don't think she felt
in the very beginning.
I'll help you with that
in a second.
I'm almost done with this.
I think we've definitely seen
Ramona's redemption this week.
I'll come and help in a second!
GERVASE:
Looks like she's turned
things around.
That's in my eyes,
she's redeemed herself.
Other people's eyes, it could be
totally different.
I think Ramona has changed
her attitude...
Well, no. Changed
her work ethic a lot.
But I don't think her attitude
has changed much.
She is working more,
she's trying,
but I think maybe it is
a little too little too late.
RAMONA:
This is what I'm like
every day when I'm feeling
like at a hundred percent.
You want to play rough, huh?
I'm feeling... good about
being a part of the group.
( grunts )
Hopefully, everyone sees, like,
"Wow. This is Ramona," you know?
"This is what, like,
a hundred percent Ramona
can offer to the team."
GREG:
The immunity challenge
will be huge today
whether the other team loses and
has to vote out another person,
then they're two people short
of what we have,
or if we have
to vote somebody out,
Uh, things should
get interesting.
I don't want to make
that trek tonight.
We got to win.
GREG:
Another
secret message?
GRETCHEN:
"The key to this challenge
is to conquer by dividing.
"On each doing the best,
"your success will be riding.
"You'll need someone to swim,
another to balance,
"a runner, a rower,
and a digger with talents.
"It's a big choice
to decide who gets where.
"Make the right moves,
"and immunity you'll share.
"Spend some time thinking,
make sure there's no doubt,
"make the wrong call,
and it could be you voted out."
JOEL:
What do you
think, Greg?
What?
Plan A, we plan everything out,
and then plan B, we throw
everything out the window
when we get there
and completely panic
and do whatever we think
we should.
GERVASE:
W Both.n.
It might be close, but we'll
definitely win today.
Without a doubt.
We got to win
this immunity challenge.
We got to stomp them so bad.
We're excited for the challenge,
we feel confident,
and we feel ready.
JOEL:
Yeah, this is a big one,
and this is huge.
Um, you know, yeah,
we don't want to lose this one.
We're here to compete,
and we're here
to win these competitions,
and we're here to do them
as a team.
I wouldn't say
we're-we're cocky.
I just think that we're,
uh, we're the best.
WelcoHey.guys.
I'll take the idol--
back up for grabs today.
Welcome to Asmara Beach.
It's a relay today,
so the sum
of all
of your individual efforts
will determine
who wins and who loses.
If one person
completely falls down
their team could crumble--
they may end up paying
for those actions tonight
at the Tribal Council.
Colleen, come on up.
Who's your...
Sean. Okay,
you guys come up here,
and I'll explain this
using this map.
There are five legs
in the relay.
The first leg is the swim.
You'll start here
and head for these buoys.
Directly underneath is
a bottle, which contains a map.
Grab the bottle
and pass it
to one of your tribe members.
For the second leg,
you'll run the bottle
across this floating bridge
into an awaiting boat.
The third leg is the paddle,
where you'll head for shore
and hand the bottle off.
Inside of it is a map
showing the destinations
for the remaining two events.
The fourth leg is
a sprint into the jungle.
Using the map, the runner
will find a rope ladder.
Climb up it,
and you'll grab a key.
For the fifth and final leg,
two members of your tribe will
locate the buried treasure chest
and dig it up.
The first team to get your chest
back on your crate
with the key in the lock
wins immunity.
ALL:
Tagi!
Pagong!
All right, guys,
thermometer's topping
100 degrees.
This is for immunity.
Whoo!
Survivors ready?
Go!
Go, Colleen, go!
Sean!
Swim, baby, swim!
Come on, Colleen.
All right!
Sean!
You're doing good, Colleen!
Come on, Sean!
Amazon women!
Oh, my God!
GERVASE:
Come on, guys, come on!
Pull!
Go, Sean!
Way to go, Joel!
Go, guys, go!
MAN:
Bring it in, now,
bring it in!
Get the bottle!
Come on, guys!
Take it!
WOMAN:
Come on, guys!
Go.
WOMAN:
You're almost there.
SUSAN:
There you go.
DIRK:
Break it!
Come on, break.
Whoa.
GRETCHEN:
Come on, Greg!
WOMAN:
Break it.
Break it!
It's open.
Got it?
You got it?
Got it.
Don't rip it.
MAN:
Go, Dirk!
Go!
RUDY:
We don't have
it yet, either.
KELLY:
Come on, you guys.
Let's go!
Dig, guys, dig!
All right, ladies,
looking good!
RAMONA:
Come on, ladies!
RICHARD:
Get the shovel
and dig around it a little bit.
It's not going
to budge.
MAN:
Don't stop!
Don't quit!
Come on, Richard,
we got our runner!
Come on, Richie!
Get it in there!
Come on!
Come on, you guys,
it's down there somewhere.
( yelling )
JOEL:
Dig in, girls,
dig in!
Dig in, dig in!
MAN:
Here he comes.
Hurry up!
Come on!
( yelping )
RAMONA:
Come on, ladies,
we got the key!
( cheering )
Run, Rudy!
Rudy! Rudy! Rudy! Rudy!
( yelling )
Come on!
Yeah! Yeah!
Put the key in it!
Come on, Rich!
( yelling )
We did our best.
That's not good enough.
The idol.
SUSAN:
Oh, yeah!
JEFF:
Tagi, nice job.
Nice job.
WOMAN:
Good job, you guys.
Pagong, I'll see you tonight--
Tribal Council.
GERVASE:
The most difficult thing
of this whole thing for me
is to vote somebody off.
I think we're dreading that.
JENNA:
Going to this island
council meeting tonight
it's really tough.
The thought of eliminating
any of these people
that we're placing
all of our confidence in,
it's getting worse.
I can't imagine
and I can't fathom
voting off somebody
from this team tonight.
I'm going, not knowing
what's going to happen,
and I'm nervous.
I wish I started slower.
And then I wish
it wasn't so far.
I'm nervous about votes
being against me tonight
because of...
I'm not a champion
in the competition.
Speed-wise,
we got right down there.
We got right down
to the treasure chest,
and it just kept collapsing in,
and it was so devastating.
All day I had this feeling
that my leg would be the one
that would lose it for us,
and it did.
It does make me feel vulnerable,
um, for the vote tonight.
GERVASE:
If somebody had to go right now
in our tribe,
I would vote for Jenna,
because she's more annoying
than Colleen.
I could deal with Jenna
not being here,
then just keep Colleen around
a little longer.
We're all friends,
and then you boot someone.
It's like the board game Sorry.
You pick the card and you got
to take your thing and smash
the other guy out of the way.
Knock 'em out, that's that,
you move on.
Sor-r-r-r-ry!
This is Tribal Council,
where each week, one member
will be voted off the island.
The last time Pagong went
to Tribal Council,
Ramona got three votes.
Is she still at risk?
nWill Gervase's weak
performances
in the last several challenges
cost him?
Or will it be someone
nobody expects?
( gong tolls )
Go ahead and take a seat.
So here we are again...
with the unpleasant task,
yet you actually have
a very tough mandate.
You have to vote one
of your tribe members
off the island tonight.
And I think what
makes it equally hard
is that in doing so,
you're sort of forced
to hold a mirror up
to yourselves.
Ramona, what criteria
do you use
in determining who you're going
to vote off the island?
Everything is so dynamic.
I mean, I could have been
thinking one person
when we left camp
and have
a totally different person
in my mind now, so...
I mean, nobody, like,
totally sucks, so...
it's like, mmm,
at this point,
I mean, we all like each other,
so it's not like...
I mean, it would
almost even be easier
if we didn't like each other
and I was like, "I hate you!
You're outta here!"
But we like each other
so it's like,
I don't know.
I mean, it's how you feel
at that time
when you go up to write
their name, it's like...
"Mmm... all right."
And you want to keep
the team strong, so...
that's probably the main thing.
Anybody feel
confident enough
that they want to own up
to feeling invincible
in tonight's vote,
certain that
when this is over,
they will be here?
( laughs )
You go, G.
I'll be around.
I'm looking to hang
till the final four.
Well, it's interesting
that you say that,
because for the last
three challenges,
you were somewhat
responsible for
your tribe's loss.
Bugging out with those
bugs, in from the deep,
swimming-- for somebody
who's still really learning
how to swim,
you took that on heartily--
and then today,
I think it says
a lot about you
that you still feel
that confident
that you aren't
going anywhere.
Nah. I feel quite comfortable
in my position on this island.
Okay. Anybody want to own up
to feeling
vulnerable tonight?
( laughter )
I think I may have just played
myself out on the last question,
so I'm feeling quite vulnerable
right now,
but, I mean,
I'll be back tomorrow.
( laughter )
Jenna, you're going
to walk over there, you're going
to pick up that pen,
you're going to write down
a name.
Is it going to feel good,
or is it going
to feel bad?
I feel guilty.
I feel bad.
Why do you feel guilty?
Well, I mean, I'm going to have
to put somebody's name down
that I really respect
and have come to really like.
It's like taking
a piece of our
family away.
You may say that it
may strengthen the
team because you take
the weakest link,
but I don't think so,
because we're so strong
right now.
You take one of us away--
I don't care who it is--
and you've got a weaker tribe.
All right. It's time to vote.
Gervase.
My vote is for Colleen.
We don't know what lies ahead
right now, but we're hurting.
So I think we need to stay
as strong as possible.
I mean, I love the girl
to death, but...
somebody's got to go,
so it's got to be for Colleen.
Self-fulfilling prophecy.
It seems time to go.
No comment.
Because even though she tried
to redeem herself,
a little too little, too late.
Before I read the votes,
I just want to remind you
that, once they're tallied,
the decision is final,
and the person
will need to leave
the island immediately.
You'll go down this bridge,
follow the path,
and about 200 feet down
is a confessional.
You can speak as long as you
like to say all your good-byes.
Sound good?
All right.
Read the votes.
First vote.
"Ramona."
"Jenna."
"Colleen."
"Ramona."
Two votes for Ramona,
two votes for Colleen.
"Mona."
Last vote.
"Ramona."
Good luck, Ramona.
Need for you to grab
your torch, Ramona.
The tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Bye, Ramona.
JEFF:
Survived another one.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Good night.
( tribal chanting )
JEFF:
Next week on Survivor:
SUSAN:
You guys wasted
three days fishing
during the day.
I don't think
Did you catch anything?
It was a waste of time, then.
It's expected to get
on each other's nerves.
Everyone's on my nerves, too,
but I just don't really
act on it.
COLLEEN:
When we go off,
it's all about sex.
It's really passionate affair
right now.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
I think the first two days
that I was sick
just really, really hurt me,
'cause those first two days
were crucial in forming
relationships and stuff,
and I really didn't get
a chance to do that
because I was so sick...
And I guess I'm signing off,
and I'm, uh... out of here.
Peace.