JEFF PROBST:
16 Americans marooned
for 39 days
in the middle
of the South China Sea.
Separated into two tribes,
Tagi and Pagong,
they competed against each
other to remain on the island,
but now the tribes
have merged into one.
Rattana is the name,
and it is everyone
for themselves.
Every third night,
the entire tribe will hike
deep into the jungle
to take part
in the Tribal Council,
where they must vote one
of their own off the island.
In the end, one will remain
and will leave the island
with $1 million in cash.
Last week on Survivor:
Yeah, bait's gone.
JEFF:
Food was scarce,
rice was being rationed...
So a can's only going
to last us two days?
They're eating that much.
JEFF:
And Rich was still
the only one providing fish.
Rich is playing a big game.
JEFF:
And so is Greg--
he cut
play-kitten Colleen loose.
GREG:
You look right
in the kitten's eye and snap
its neck-- it's nothing
personal, you're hungry.
JEFF:
And made a move on Rich.
RICHARD:
He' That's great.ing.
JEFF:
The reward challenge
brought videos from home...
Hi, Daddy.
Baby.
JEFF:
Except for Jenna.
Oh, don't...
It would've done wonders to see
that my kids are okay.
GERVASE:
She's tugging on people's
emotions right there
and that's a threat for me.
JEFF:
And at Tribal Council...
Is there an alliance?
Do I have to answer?
No, I'm just kidding.
No, no.
JEFF:
Last week, Greg was voted off.
Eight castaways remain.
Who will be voted off tonight?
That was my deal--
out of here.
Well, I don't know
if they were...
RICHARD:
Outright lying
is absolutely essential,
especially when you have
a host like Jeff,
who's as bold as to ask
"Well, so Sue, tell me,
is there an alliance?"
What a question.
You think
I'm going to come out and say
"Oh, yeah, we got four of us
voting up against all you guys.
We're going to knock you all
down to the end." Come on.
It won't be
bad if you get
in the water.
COLLEEN:
Those people flat out lied
in front of a national
television audience.
I mean,
they want a million bucks
and they're going to get it...
And I loved Jeff's question
"Is, uh, a deserving person
going to win this money?"
The answer to that question
is "no."
How you doing this
morning, Kelly?
I'm doing.
I didn't really sleep
last night.
No?
KELLY:
This whole alliance thing
is getting too stupid
and too crazy.
If we stick with it,
it's just like lining lambs
to the slaughter.
Who goes next? Who goes...?
like, that's no fun.
We were targeted
already, anyway.
If we keep
annoying them
like we are,
we're going to be
gone really soon.
KELLY:
Yeah, I don't like it.
I-I'm not happy playing
the game that way.
If I'm going to win,
if I'm really going to be
the last survivor,
if I'm really going to survive
and really do this,
then it has to be on my own.
SEAN:
Rich is definitely
in this very good
strategic position
for himself, I think.
He's worked hard.
Well, not that hard.
Just happens to be good
at spearfishing.
He doesn't do much else.
He sure don't do a damn thing
around here except fish.
SEAN:
But he's a good sport.
I mean, we call him all kinds
of names and make fun of him.
I sort of liked him
before I knew he was queer.
Lost a prong to a good,
five-foot nurse shark.
I got to take them
by hand from now on,
like Tarzan-style--
wrestle them.
He's in an ideal position,
'cause I think
he's the epicenter
of the power right now.
He's bringing in the fish.
Oh, my God.
There's got to be 25 pounds
or 20 pounds of fish here.
It's all about
the fish, man.
The fish don't
influence me, though.
No?
Not in the least.
You can take the heavy-duty
equipment and I'll putz.
Okay.
'Cause I fed you today.
Yeah.
SEAN:
I love Rich, I really do.
He's been a great asset
to this camp,
but he is a little immature
in his motives at times.
You'll be so damn full
of protein after this meal,
you won't know
what to do with yourself.
This is funny.
I am...
the master.
He's very protective
about spearing fish
and he brings it up
at every island council:
"I'm catching fish.
Don't vote me off."
It's an insecurity aspect
to him.
The last island Tribal Council
when I was talking about, um...
"I'll be staying around here
because I'm providing fish"
was an outright blatant lie.
I'm staying around here
'cause I'm bright.
It has nothing to do
with catching fish.
That is a
lot of fish.
RICHARD:
Catching fish
makes people happy,
but that's not why
they're voting me here.
They're not voting me off
because I'm not letting them.
SUSAN:
Tell me if
I'm doing it...
like cutting
too much meat.
RICHARD:
No, you're doing pretty well.
Got it.
Now rip it out.
I'm sorry, I can't...
You want
to do one?
COLLEEN:
Do you see them
bringing these stingrays
and stuff in?
They're, like,
still flapping around
and they take this dull knife,
and chop off their head.
It's disgusting.
( loud slapping )
If I choose
to watch my dinner
that came from the sea
be killed or not be killed,
I would rather not
watch it be killed.
JENNA:
Rich, you're the man.
You are the reef master.
Yeah, there's some water
over here.
JENNA:
Oh, I'm so
looking forward
to this now.
I wouldn't even eat fish sticks.
SUSAN:
I'm just hungry.
I could care
less about that.
When Rich came in
with a fish,
I said to Rudy, "I should go
and stoke that fire up."
And Rudy's, like, "Oh, no,
no, no, that's good enough.
It's hot enough,"
and it wasn't hot enough.
RICHARD:
Well, I would say
it's done, Rudy,
and black.
It curls up
into little balls.
I know.
SUSAN:
The fish is tough to cook
because they cooked
a little bit
and then they cooled off
and they had to start
the fire back up
and cook the fish again,
so Rich is sort of irritated.
( rhythmic tapping )
RICHARD:
Rudy's clueless
when it comes to fish, and, um,
you know, really ruined it.
You ready?
Yep.
RICHARD:
Nobody knew what to do
with cooking the fish
and so it sits here
and it sits half on the heat,
and it sits over there
and it gets turned over
halfway and it doesn't,
and so it's half-cooked
and overcooked and undercooked
and half of the fish,
half of the three rays
were wasted...
and that infuriates me.
It's overdone.
It's charcoal.
Its wings are curled up.
It's very, very easy
to put a fire together
that's nice and hot.
Just 'cause I see
how to do that
doesn't mean anybody else
should know how, so...
I was sitting there, just
pissed off, really frustrated.
I don't want anybody around
I don't want anybody near me
when I'm frustrated,
and people are sitting there,
"What's wrong?"
and that just makes it worse.
GERVASE:
Don't be hard
on yourself.
Huh?
Just take it easy--
let us be hard on you.
Okay. Go for it, dude.
GERVASE:
Don't you know how
a fire works, man?
RICHARD:
Uh-huh, I do...
and I'm not really patient
about teaching anybody,
so I'm just going
to do it myself from now on.
I probably won't get fish,
actually, for a
little while now,
anyway, because they need
to appreciate it.
I'm bringing in too many
right now.
I brought in a bunch yesterday
and a bunch today
and so we need
to take a break
and let them kind of hunger
for it again.
COLLEEN:
So many times Rich opens
his mouth,
and I just want to be, like,
"Oh, be quiet over there
in the corner.
"You're not making any sense,
and you think you're so smart
"and you're... just go home,
and go get your liposuction
and go catch more fish,
'cause you're bugging me."
You know, he thinks
he's so above everybody
and is full of baloney, really.
RICHARD:
Pathetic, burnt, overdone
wasteful again.
Amazes me.
KELLY:
The hardest part now is...
( sighs )
...the food.
We're hungry
and Rich is the only one
that can fish.
You got to go out
an hour before it gets dark
and then, right at
when it was getting dark,
we started getting our bites
and then, after it got dark,
we didn't get no more bites.
We've gone fishing
in the morning.
We've gone in the afternoon...
at night.
We're not catching any fish.
SUSAN:
I'm getting
to the point
if there ain't
no crabs out there
in a day or two,
I ain't gonna to do it no more.
It bothers me
that I can't get my own food,
that I have to rely
on someone else.
Ooh, big fish.
Oh, wow!
We got a fish, you guys, right?
It's a fish, for sure.
Whoo!
That's so awesome.
Look at that thing.
He's pretty big.
Fish!
Bloop.
SUSAN:
Good proof
that we can get the fish.
We caught a fish today,
finally-- yes!--
and it feels so good.
I feel so accomplished now.
JENNA:
I think, uh,
it disappointed Rich
that us girls
kept these crab traps going
and that we caught a fish.
That's good.
He's going to make
a big point
"Oh, that ain't a lot
to feed you,"
but it's a point
that we did catch it.
So, I don't give a ( blip )
about how he's going to see it.
We caught it;
I feel accomplished.
We've done it all now.
We got a fish, man,
a edible fish.
I ain't kidding you.
RUDY:
Big one?
SUSAN:
Yeah, pretty
nice size.
RUDY:
Is he kicking?
Yeah, he's
still alive.
Yeah, he's still alive.
Yeah, that's a good one.
I know it.
SUSAN:
But, yeah,
he's going to be...
I think it might bother him.
In a way, I hope it does.
I hope it bugs him,
'cause now he can't
say that no more, you know?
'Cause us girls
caught this one.
( buzzing )
Oh, wow.
I love getting mail
and there was a log hanging
above our mailbox.
It looked an awful lot like
part of the tree,
but when I took it down,
there was a sign on there
a little a nursery rhyme,
it says:
"If you can make like a monkey,
"then you'll be home free,
"if you want barbecue for lunch,
then go climb a tree."
Somebody's eating
a barbecue.
That sounds like fun.
Shish kebob!
SEAN:
I'm sure the game is
anything but simple,
just, like,
just pick a rope and run.
Hey, look who it is!
Hey, Jeff.
Well, here's the deal.
I thought today,
we'd switch it up a little
and show you the carrot,
the reward, before the challenge
so you guys know
exactly what it is...
Listen to
your stomach.
You're going for.
Are you
smelling this?
This is
today's reward.
Oh, man!
JEFF:
Some good, old-fashioned,
American barbecue.
We got it all.
All this stuff, here...
Look at that,
a lot of meat.
Steak and a hot dog.
JEFF:
Some kebobs.
We got your buns...
your chips.
A little something
to remind you of home.
And since we're talking
about home...
Why not?
Love letters from home.
Jenna, yours on top.
Oh, I got one!
I'm so excited.
JEFF:
One of you guys gets
a great barbecue,
you get to read your
letter from home,
and does it get any
better than that?
Sound good?
GERVASE:
I was shaking
when I saw the food.
I started shaking
because I'm, like,
"That's real chicken."
Now think about that
and then think about rice.
I'm thinking,
how am I going
to get my grubby
little hands
on some of
them burgers.
I'm prepared
to eat rice tonight...
( chuckles )
like every night.
I want the letter from home more
because I can go back
and get rice,
but I haven't seen
or heard anything from my kids.
That's it, I'm going big,
going for all of it.
No offense, Jeff, but if I win,
you're going hungry, bud,
'cause I'm not sharing.
Then, let's go do this thing
and come back and eat.
Man, oh, man.
I want this stuff.
JEFF:
Here's the deal:
basically, it's a ropes course.
There are 16 legs.
On each one of them is
a medallion with your number.
You guys have all been
pre-assigned a number.
Pretty simple-- you got to get
through all of them,
grab a medallion from each one.
First person back here
on this platform
with all 16 of their medallions
gets the barbecue.
If you fall off the course,
you're out.
Sound good?
Everybody get ready.
You got an eye
on where you're going?
Get up here on the
ring, Sean... buddy.
Yeah.
Survivors, ready?!
Go!
Aah!
( laughing )
You got time, Rich.
Five, five, five.
JEFF:
Good job, Rich.
Your first medallion.
Keep it up,
Colleen.
You're in
second place.
Okay, so I love being tall.
JEFF:
Try to keep
mental notes
of where you've been
and where you've
still got to go.
Careful, Jenna.
Keep it up, Sean.
12 more to go.
Doing great, Rudy--
fifth place.
Come on,
I got to go under you.
Ready?
All right?
Yep.
JEFF:
Good work together,
guys, on the ladder.
Keep at it, Rudy.
You're still
in the lead, Kelly.
Oh, no.
Done!
You got to get back
here to the platform.
Okay, is anybody
else finished?
Oh, that's me!
Colleen or Kelly--
first one back
here wins.
( squeals )
Colleen.
Yeah!
JEFF:
Nice job.
( all talking excitedly )
That was awesome!
Yeah!
Colleen, right here.
Good job, Colleen.
We've got
this great barbecue--
it looked pretty good...
a lot of food--
we've got a great letter
from home.
How about
inviting...
Everybody!
Don't even make
me pick one.
JEFF:
I do want you to pick one
person to come with us...
Do they get
the letter, too?
JEFF:
This person will
get their letter
and this person
will also get
all the food.
( clicking tongue )
( chuckling )
Jenna is going
to hear from her kids.
Good work.
That wasn't
a tough decision, was it?
She didn't get a video.
Thank you
so much.
JEFF:
Very nice gesture.
So, you guys can, um,
sadly head back to camp
and we're going to head down
to the beach
and have a barbecue.
Enjoy it, guys.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Okay.
( laughing )
Listen to what
Sean says today...
What did he say?
He goes, "Well..."
'cause they voted four
against Dirk
when he wasn't there.
Then they voted four
against Gretchen
and then it's, like,
they voted six
against... but obviously,
four against Greg,
and he's, like,
"If it happens one more time,
I know..."
and I was, like,
"What are you talking about?
It's happened three times."
I mean, what's going on?
But, see, Sean's the...
Sean's the swing vote,
you know what I mean?
'Cause you, me and Gervase
could definitely
do something.
They're going
to pick people off
until it gets down to them
and then they're going
to start eating each other,
you know what I mean?
But I'm saying, like,
why are we sitting back
and watching it happen?
So, let's do it.
( chuckling )
JEFF:
All right,
here are your letters.
You read yours first.
Oh, mine's so thick.
I love it.
Go on
and read yours.
Oh, my God.
Oh, they're drawings!
Oh, my...
( laughing and crying )
Oh, my God.
How cute.
Yeah, we have them
all over the house.
( sniffles )
My car interior windows
are decorated
with stickers
I can no longer get off.
"I'm proud of you...
super, wonderful, hooray."
Yep.
( sniffling )
Happy birthday, Rich.
RICHARD:
Thanks, Suzy Q.
SEAN:
Rich's birthday
is today,
and it's his 39th birthday
and he celebrated immediately
by taking off
all of his clothes
and celebrating
in his birthday suit...
which you never get used
to seeing Richard naked.
( laughs )
RICHARD:
I'm 39 today
and I had intended
for quite a long time
to celebrate my birthday naked.
And I'm sure he does love
to be naked,
and I'm glad for that
and I thought I'd be okay
with that,
but sitting at the fire
this morning
and he comes just walking up
and sits, like,
two inches from me
naked...
I wanted to get away.
All the nakedness,
( laughing )
I'm just having a problem
with this nakedness.
It felt awkward
sitting next to a naked gay man,
and if he had, like, something
to cover the butt crack area
I'd be cool with that.
RUDY:
When I go home,
my wife asks me about--
"Well, who was with you?"
I'll say, "A queer
that ran around bare-ass
half of the time,"
for one thing.
( laughing )
COLLEEN:
Rich wanted to be naked
for his birthday.
Oh, fun.
Show off a little more.
I mean, he was doing it
for shock value.
It's goofy.
Who walks around naked 24/7?
I think you were doing
it for shock value.
RICHARD:
For shock value?
Is it shock value?
I don't know
if it's shock value or not.
Colleen was particularly
uncomfortable with my nakedness
and when she saw me naked,
she just made a funny face
and put her hands over her face
and who knows what that's
intended to signal?
I said to you, like,
"Oh, my God, Rich."
But if I lived my life
based on what
made other people
uncomfortable,
I wouldn't be
liviMy life.fe.
COLLEEN:
I love that Rich gets annoyed
with me--
that makes me happy--
and he really has
in the past two days
and it just makes me want
to egg him on more.
Oh, big deal.
Who gives a crap?
I'm naked, whoopee.
( laughing )
( seabirds screeching )
Oh, yes, we have a clue.
"Our next challenge is
a battle of wit
"Just make sure
there's always
"a new square to hit,
"being immune
at the council
"is what it's about,
"paint yourself
in a corner
and you'll find
yourself out."
( squeals )
Ooh, we get
to play mind games now...
Not that we're
not playing mind games now.
It's crunch time now.
It's getting down
to the final wire
and I'm amazed
that I'm still here
and I got 12 days left.
"Our next challenge
is a battle of wit..."
It's not even a strategy.
I'm just really focused now,
on winning these challenges.
"Paint yourself in..."
kind of like twister.
GERVASE:
I'm trying to think,
"How did I lose yesterday
and how can I stop that
from happening again today?"
'Cause today is even bigger
than the food
when it comes down to it.
You know, I'd rather not eat
and get that immunity challenge
every time.
I know the only way
I'm going to stay
is to win the challenges, so...
that's the only thing
I'm worried about.
That's the only thing
I'm focusing on
is winning the challenges.
I think it's a fair system.
I think you're
a perfect example.
I'm glad I decided
to not go back
for the alphabetical order
after you won immunity
'cause it gives the contestant
an out to avoid my vote.
I think it adds
a new dimension to the game,
me going alphabetically.
COLLEEN:
( laughs )
SEAN:
Yeah?
Yeah, did you know
that we're going by Zelda now?
Zoey.
SEAN:
Yeah, Zoey and Zelda.
Why? Why do
you want that?
Uh, alphabetical reasons.
Oh.
I'm going in alphabetical
order-- Jenna is next.
It would make me happy
if Gervase does not win immunity
this time
'cause I had
to skip him last time--
you know,
I skipped him in the order--
and maybe Jenna will win it
and get out of the order.
I know it's nice
that if you win immunity,
you get skipped
and then you never get
in the rotation, like Ger.
JENNA:
Oh, you're out
of the rotation?
Ger is out of the rotation.
Yeah. I'm next.
KELLY:
Sean's going around
telling everybody
"Don't be in the alliance.
Don't..." um...
"vote your conscience."
Meanwhile, he's going around
preaching everyone
to vote their conscience
and he's, like,
"Oh, okay, alphabetically."
SEAN:
My votes are going
to go alphabetical.
So, today's Jenna.
If I'm going
to be the swing vote--
which I don't think
I will be--
then I won't vote for her,
obviously.
GERVASE:
Sean... I like Sean.
Sean's a great guy, you know,
but about Sean's
alphabetical order.
It's like my granddaddy
used to say:
"If you want to be seen,
stand up,
"If you want to be heard,
speak up,
and if you want
to be appreciated, shut up."
I'm just going to stay
in alphabetical order.
It's all I can do.
We've tested
your physical strength,
your swimming ability,
your agility,
your speed... all that.
Today is something
a little different.
It's up here, in your head.
This is a game
that requires strategy.
It's a lot like chess,
a little bit
like tic-tac-toe,
but unlike chess,
where you're taking one person,
you've got seven people
to think about.
The way the game works is
you'll start on a square
and you'll simply,
one at a time, on my cue
move to another square,
turning the square over
behind you.
As long
as you can keep stepping
to another square,
you're still alive,
but when you run out
of red squares
to step on, you're out.
So now, if you just flip over
these squares here,
we'll determine
the order.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, yes.
Now, in any particular order,
step on one
of the flower squares.
It does not matter.
These are all even
when you begin.
So, Rich, you're up first.
Perfect. Rudy.
Sean.
Gervase, to you.
Sue.
Colleen.
Kelly.
Jenna.
Sue.
Colleen.
Yeah... I'm out!
JEFF:
Take a step back
and flip
that one over.
There you go.
Take a seat
on the log.
That full meal
has got you...
sated.
All right... Kelly.
Jenna-- out on the island
by herself.
Kelly.
SUSAN:
Just had to get
in the center.
Looks like you're out,
Kelly.
Just doing my part.
JEFF:
Join Colleen
over there.
Jenna.
Rich.
I'm out.
Sue, you're out.
All right.
Jenna.
Sean, you foiled my plan.
SEAN:
Sorry, baby.
Was that your
plan, Sean?
No. Well, yeah, once she
got behind me, yeah, yeah.
To block her?
Rich.
You need to worry
about yourself, Hatch.
No, there's nothing
I can do.
I'm whimpering
into nowhere-land, here...
Rudy.
Slowly
dying...
the wise old man
is looking good.
Sean.
Oh, no, Sean,
no, Sean.
Don't you know
you're dead, Sean?
You're ruining it.
You got 50 million.
She won't last, Sean.
Rudy will last longer.
He'll have to kill me.
Otherwise, I could
have bebopped around.
Sorry. I'm doing what
I think is right.
JEFF:
Gervase.an...
Bad move, Sean.
You could have gotten Rudy
out of there.
No, he
Yes, he could have.
All right, Rich.
Rudy.
Rudy has many
more options.
Down there.
He's doing right.
You should've
diagonal so...
Don't listen
to her, Rudy.
She's trying to
trick you, Rudy.
Shut up.
I am not.
It's those young girls,
Rudy,
trying to get
in your head.
Stay strong,
Rudy.
JENNA:
Is it my turn?
Gervase.
Still alive.
Jenna, you,
unfortunately,
are not.
You're out.
I figured
you are.
Yoo-haw!
JEFF:
Rich, turn over
your last tile--
you're done.
Bye!
Rudy, it's down
to you three
for immunity from
tonight's vote.
Go sidewards!
Go left, Rudy, go left!
GERVASE:
No coaching
from the side.
No, no, no.
Directly to your left.
GERVASE:
To the right, Rudy!
Take... take...
No, left, Rudy,
because then you
have down here...
Up to the right, Rudy.
She's trying to trick you.
No, no, no,
no, buddy.
This one.
Yeah, there
you go.
Good job, Rudy.
Gervase.
Ain't gonna work.
You've won, Rudy,
if you take that path.
SUSAN:
If you go at a
diagonal across,
you got more squares
than him to land on.
JENNA:
You've got more squares left.
There you go!
SUSAN:
There you go.
Yeah, now you're
heading up to the beach.
I think it's
a foregone
conclusion.
( sighs )
Flip that over,
Gervase.
JENNA:
Good job, Rudy.
SUSAN:
There you go.
You got it, Rudy.
Hang tight, buddy.
We're going to be
taking that tile
from you any minute.
( cheering )
JEFF:
Rudy, you win.
Take the honor of
flipping the rest
of these over for me.
( buzzing )
Tonight's going
to be interesting.
Oh, yeah?
SUSAN:
Really, when they
first got here,
they were
really ambitious.
Now you can see
their ambition's
kind of, like,
filtering a little bit.
If I feel like sitting
in a hammock all day,
I'm going to sit
in a hammock all day.
I'm not going
to stop you.
No.
COLLEEN:
We had fun, you know?
We had-- Pagong was a good,
was a good place to live.
Now we moved
into the new neighborhood
with the nasty neighbors.
( grunting )
SUSAN:
I want to go over
in my house for
awhile and bitch.
COLLEEN:
Then we came in here
like, "Maybe we can
all be friends"
and they came in, like,
"We can smash 'em."
Yes, they did.
COLLEEN:
The people who came in swinging
were Rich and Sue.
They knew.
They're smart.
They're very smart people...
Although Rich
is just a numbskull. God!
RICHARD:
All you 16, 15 weirdoes
are making me nutty.
I'm losing my mind.
COLLEEN:
People are wishy-washy.
They're conniving
and they're stupid,
and that's what's happening,
and it's all out in the open
for everybody to see.
The decision
that I feel I'm left with is
do I interact
with these people, have fun
and just wait
till my ticket comes up
or do I try and strategize
and try and make a difference?
It's so sad now.
You know, we just wait,
you know?
Unless...
we think of something.
( whistling )
Yesterday, at the dinner,
we had a whole conversation
about forming a new alliance.
Yeah, shh...
We're going to vote the same
and we figure that this puts us
in jeopardy for the next one,
but we were
in jeopardy anyway, so...
GERVASE:
Well, we tried
the "be nice, honor" way.
It didn't work,
so don't be stupid anymore.
It's just, we're smarter now.
We saw that
that way didn't work,
so we got to switch gears.
COLLEEN:
What if I
just had this
as a skirt?
Oh, that's killer!
GERVASE:
I don't think
models even wear
skirts that short.
JENNA:
Go for it, Colleen!
Wear it!
Not doing that, Sue?
Jenna and I were just,
you know, goofing off
and, uh, Kelly decided
to join in.
I feel bad for Kelly
because she wants to play.
And Rich is, like,
"Something's happened to you
"since these girls came.
I'm really worried about you,"
kind of putting her in her place
and makes her feel
a little self-conscious.
By her being nervous
and wishy-washy
about where her loyalties lie,
it's really making
Sue and Rich nervous.
You're young.
You hung out
with the chicks.
There's more Pagong members
than Tagi members
and the Pagong members...
Pagong members don't
like any of us.
They like you a lot better
than any of us.
Kelly's acting a little odd.
She's dressing like
the other two that are her age,
and I'm hoping
that Kelly hasn't, uh,
shifted trust
and-and joined forces
with somebody else.
All them girls
are dressed the same today.
SEAN:
Yeah, they're dressing
like, uh, superheroes.
RUDY:
Like who?
Superheroes.
They were dancing around here
a little while ago.
It looked like
the third grade.
I thought
about a female alliance
and watching them,
the way they walk around,
hand in hand.
I even thought about lesbianism,
but, uh, maybe not.
I don't know.
And, uh, it could happen
if they had any brains,
but I don't think they got
enough brains to do that.
I move objects with my mind,
but only I can see it.
KELLY:
I probably will have
the swing vote tonight.
I'd said before, you know,
alliance or no alliance,
there's two people that I have
in mind to vote off
and they're two people that,
um, are-are competition,
but, um, they annoy me
and... ( chuckling )
they're kind of sucky
to live with.
Let's roll, Gervase.
Get out of here.
COLLEEN:
I really don't know
what's going to happen
at Tribal Council tonight.
I know I'm voting for Rich.
I know Jenna's voting for Rich.
I know Gervase
is voting for Rich.
GERVASE:
As long as he's catching fish,
people are gonna try
to keep him around,
so I say, get rid of Rich
and we all starve together.
JENNA:
The rest of my alliance,
if that's what
you want to call it?
Yeah, we're all voting for Rich.
He's ruthless
and the fact that we're voting
him out on his birthday--
it's not lost on me.
We're giving him
a birthday present.
Okay, let's do this, Brutus!
Gotta go.
JEFF:
Today's immunity challenge
saw wisdom and strategy
outplay youth and strength.
Tonight it's Rudy
who's safe from the vote
as the others
contemplate their fate.
But this is not
the only vote on their mind.
Beginning tonight with Greg,
all members voted off the island
will return
to subsequent Tribal Councils
as part of a jury.
They will gather information
for a very important decision,
because, ultimately,
these seven will decide
who, of the final two survivors,
leaves the island
with the million-dollar prize.
( gong clanging )
You're back.
Tribal Council
number nine.
27 days you guys
have been here.
At the last
Tribal Council,
we established
our core group of nine,
so from that
two of you will make
it to the final vote.
The other seven
will form a jury that
will really decide
that final vote.
Now, in order to make
an informed decision,
the jury needs
information.
So, beginning tonight, Greg
will be joining us here
as part of the jury.
He's merely here
to observe, gather
information
that he'll base
his decision on
and at each tribal
council, when somebody
else is voted off,
they will return to join Greg.
Happy birthday
to you, Mr. Hatch.
Thanks, Jeff.
Something we talked about today.
You were going to spend the day
in your birthday suit.
That was part of your original
idea, anyway.
Yep.
A couple of people
voiced concern
that, uh, "Maybe
I don't like this."
Well, I just enjoy
being nude.
I'm on a deserted island in the
middle of the South China Sea.
I thought, what better place?
What better place than
to just hang out nude?
But it did make a couple
of people uncomfortable
so I thought,
"Why bother?"
Sean. I got to ask you
about the alphabet thing.
The alphabet.
Give me the rationale so I'm
absolutely clear on it.
The rationale
is many-fold.
First of all,
it gives me an order
that I can follow
pretty easily--
that's always nice.
And it is strategic.
If you look at the order,
the actual alphabet,
a lot of the Pagong people
in the beginning,
a lot of Tagi people
in the end.
This tortures me.
Every three days. I hate it.
Jenna, what's
your take on that?
I'm next.
I'm today.
That's true.
Yes. I'm "J."
That's, that's cool.
She knows she wouldn't
take it personally
and I think
she's a safe vote tonight.
If I was... felt
she was in jeopardy,
I would think twice
at the very least
of casting a vote.
Sue, what's your
take on that
as somebody who
might come up soon
in the alphabet
and get a vote
against you
even if Sean
thinks you're the
greatest person here?
Oh, Sean just...
he's neurotic.
He's just, he's an idiot.
SEAN:
Thanks a lot, Sue.
Thank you very much.
It's like, wow, okay,
so I'm next, you know?
That's the way he votes,
that's the way he votes.
I... I just think he just...
I don't know, that
or he doesn't have
enough balls to make a decision.
I don't have
a malicious bone in my body
and I think that
casting a vote,
it makes me
feel malicious.
I want to avoid it.
Yeah, but you came
into this knowing...
knowing you were going
to have to do this.
Me, I've changed my vote
like, three times
within the last two hours.
And now it's me, right?
( laughing )
No. No.
How important
is Richard right now?
He seems to be the only guy--
at least of who's left--
that's able
to catch fish.
No. We did today.
Trapped it.
We nailed a fish today
in the trap.
They got a fish.
SUSAN:
We got a fish today.
A nice-sized fish.
I'm outta here.
We gave it
to Richard for his birthday.
All right, it's
time to vote.
Gervase.
My vote's for Rich
because the longer Rich is
on this island,
the bigger of a threat
he becomes to me
taking that million dollars,
so I figure
if I get rid of him now,
everybody else will be cake,
so, happy birthday, Rich.
Eliminating a big mouth.
Continuing my alphabetic
strategy,
Jenna, you know I love you,
no offense to this.
I hope you don't get voted off.
I don't think...
you might have one vote or two
votes or something like that
but nothing major,
I don't think. I hope.
Fish or not, I think
he's getting near the point,
he's ready to go home.
Even though it is his birthday.
JEFF:
As always,
your identity
at Tribal Council is noted
by your fire, your torch.
Directly across from you
are the eight torches
of the first eight people
voted off.
Tonight, another torch will be
added to that group
and that person will join Greg
next week as part of our jury.
I'll go tally the votes.
I just want to remind you
that once the votes are tallied,
the decision is final.
The person will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
Now I'll read the votes.
That's three votes for Jenna,
three votes for Rich.
The last vote...
"J" for Jenna.
Jenna, you need to bring
your torch over.
Jenna, the tribe
has spoken.
It's time for
you to go.
Thanks.
Good-bye.
Jenna is now part
of the jury.
She'll return next week
and join Greg.
The rest of you
can head back to camp.
Good night.
Next wee A cigar!vivor...
Good news for Gervase.
Hey, everybody, it's a boy!
Having left the alliance,
will Kelly now vote
against them?
You're seeming
more down.
KELLY:
And if I'm going to do
something conniving and dirty,
let's get Rich off.
Me and Kelly are
taking him down.
Well, I had a good time.
It was a great time
on the island.
I felt like I was
targeted tonight
because they knew that
Sean would vote for me
alphabetically,
so they knew they'd get
an easy off with me.
They were more
powerful because
Pagong went into it
a little naive,
so, that's it.
I had
a really good time,
and no hard feelings
and nothing's
taken personally.