JEFF PROBST:
16 Americans forced to
abandon ship
in the middle
of the South China sea...
Marooned for 39 days,
they must work together
to build shelter, find food
and survive the island
but, ultimately,
it is everyone for themselves.
Every third night
they will hike
deep into the jungle
to take part
in the Tribal Council
where they must vote
one of their own
off the island.
In the end,
only one will remain,
and will leave the island
with $1 million in cash.
( primal call echoing )
Last week on Survivor...
( thunder crashing )
RAMONA:
It was the worst night
I've ever slept.
Gretchen decided
she wouldn't sleep
one more night
in their poorly constructed
shelter.
I don't want to sleep
in that anymore.
I don't want to
be antisocial
but I'm going
in the woods.
JEFF:
Ramona felt like an outcast
and wanted to redeem herself.
Want to play rough, huh?
JENNA:
She's trying,
but I think maybe it is
a little too little too late.
JEFF:
At Tagi tribe, Sue continued
her quest to find more food...
Tapioca. Tapioca's supposed
to have red lines and...
Got to find the tapioca.
While Sean worked
on other island necessities.
SEAN:
I had this vision.
I thought I'd build myself
a bowling alley
right about here.
SUSAN:
Sean sits there for five hours
and builds his bowling alley.
I'm tired of feeding people
that don't do anything.
My parents would be so proud.
JEFF:
A cunning plan was hatched
by Sue, Kelly and Rich.
RICH:
So, the, um...
alliances have begun.
The whole point
of forming an alliance is so
we're all going to vote
the same way.
JEFF:
Tagi was on a roll.
They won
the reward challenge...
Go get it.
And, then...
the Immunity Challenge.
( cheering )
So, a distraught Pagong tribe
had to return
to Tribal Council.
GERVASE:
The most difficult thing for me
was to vote somebody off.
JEFF:
And even though Ramona
had been working
harder than ever,
she was still voted off.
Last vote: Ramona.
The tribe
has spoken.
12 people left.
Who will be voted off next?
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
( primal chanting )
( birds chirping )
COLLEEN:
We slept late
for the first time
since we've been here today.
Everybody's a little bit
on edge.
Everybody's
a little vulnerable today.
( insects buzzing )
JOEL:
I think today
we're just a little bit down
because another person's gone,
of course,
and we can see
that the group's getting
a little bit smaller.
Even if it's
only two people smaller,
it's still getting
a little bit smaller
and, uh, and we're starting
to see that a little bit.
JENNA:
For some reason,
the last two to three days
we've just been really down.
I think it's got a lot to do
with just, uh,
we lost two in a row.
We lost a member of the group
and one of...
who I consider
one of our male leaders, Greg,
was really feeling terrible.
He's got an ear infection.
He's really sick.
GRETCHEN:
I think the camp looks trashy.
I think stuff's
all over the place.
I think the flag should be up.
I mean,
there's a lot we could do
to make
this camp look really nice.
I mean, something's going
to have to change.
Something's going to have
to happen
to make everybody decide
to pitch in.
Welcome to the big top,
ladies and gentlemen.
RUDY:
That is the parachute
that they dropped
the cargo with the other day
that, uh,
contained some goodies
and, uh, right now, they want
to hang the parachute up
for shade.
KELLY:
Me, personally,
I was a little irritated
with, um, Sean and Dirk's effort
around camp.
I mean,
they try to go fishing
when they know they're
not going to catch anything
and I think, personally,
it's just so they can say,
"Hey, well, we did something."
Kelly thinks that failure
to catch fish is failure to try.
You know, I think she's equating
those two, which is not true.
Right now we
could be working...
driving through
rush hour traffic.
Yep.
Fighting bills
and trying
to get dates.
Instead we're just chilling
on the South China sea.
SEAN:
The fish are not biting
hooks out here for some reason.
Either we got the wrong bait, or
we're going at the wrong time.
Fishing with a hook, I think,
is useless.
They put about 25 hours in
and not a bite.
That's a big enough hint for me
not to go fishing with a hook.
You guys getting
anything?
SEAN:
Not even a nibble.
It's our
day off, brother.
SUSAN:
I'm just irritated
with Sean and Dirk
going out and wasting
three days
in the daylight fishing.
And I let them know, too.
During the day, you should
go out in the woods
looking for tapioca
and fish at night.
You guys wasted
three days fishing
during the day.
DIRK:
I don't think
it was a waste.
Well, did you catch
anything?
No, ma'am.
Okay.
It was a waste of time then.
SEAN:
It's expected to get on
each other's nerves.
Maybe everyone's
on my nerves, too,
but I just
don't really act on it.
I just wanted to be happy--
have a nice life here
and that's it.
KELLY:
It's been the people who really
work and contribute to camp
versus the people
who are lazy
and don't really do anything
to contribute to the camp.
The second I stop having fun
I'll vote myself off the island.
I came here
to have a great time,
grow in my faith
with the Lord
and that's the most important
thing to me.
RUDY:
It's funny to me that a guy
would read the Bible out here.
The only reason
I'd bring a Bible is if...
I mean, I'm religious too...
if I needed toilet paper.
Come on over, guys.
I bring news
of tomorrow's challenge.
Right here.
"First Annual
"Weapons Target
Shooting Classic.
The battle in Borneo."
Now, it's
a reward challenge,
so you'll be competing
against the other tribe
for something I have
a feeling you
all want-- food.
So here's
the deal.
It'll be three rounds.
First round is
a blowgun.
Five darts.
Second round--
a mighty slingshot
and the third round,
spear tossing.
So you'll pick one person
for each event.
So only three people
will participate.
And I'm coming to bring these
so you can practice.
I love it.
SEAN:
We had a little visit
from Jeff, our host, today,
and he came by and told us
that tomorrow's going
to be a competition--
a reward challenge.
So we've been practicing
all day at that.
( laughing )
( cheering )
Right in the coconut.
That wasn't too bad.
Turns out that I'm pretty good
with the blowgun.
And I never really...
never shot a blowgun before
in my life.
Dead on. Good.
Turns out Rich is
an expert marksman.
Something
we didn't know about him
until today, so, uh...
He has excellent aim
when it comes to a slingshot.
No worries.
Yeah, I think he's
slingshot boy.
And Sue throws that spear
much better than any
of the guys in our tribe.
She's a wild woman
with the spear.
I always wanted to kill a pig
with a javelin... with a spear.
And I was kind of hoping
that I'd be good at nothing
so that I could just,
like, hang back
and let the pressure go
on somebody else.
Turns out I throw
the javelin the best.
I'm thinking the other team's
going to have a guy
throwing the spear.
So if there is,
there's a good chance
that I can dog some guy
on national TV.
Cool.
No matter who
they put up,
you got it.
SUE:
Even if we lost
and I at least dogged the guy
in the spear throwing,
they'd be happy.
GERVASE:
Next up, out of Green Bay,
weighing in at 2...
excuse me,
he lost 20 pounds. 180.
Big country
all-American,
the world's strongest man!
( quacking )
I never really threw
a spear in my life.
Except, you know...
anything serious.
It's kind of hard
to keep it straight.
That's a good distance,
especially a little thing
like this,
and you don't know if you can
take a running start
or how you should do it,
or what the thing is, so
this looks like it's going to be
our weakest event for sure.
Because the other girls have
the blowguns down really well.
The slingshot looks good.
So it would be nice
to win it today.
A lot of these reward challenges
we haven't really been after,
but I think we're all really
determined for this one.
Looks good.
( cheering )
Welcome to the First Annual
Survivor Weapons Challenge,
otherwise known
as The Battle in Borneo.
It's three rounds--
first round is blow darts.
You guys have selected
your blow dart shooters?
All right,
you guys'll have ten darts.
Go ahead
and take your shot here.
Tagi, over here;
Pagong over here to watch.
Any of the fruit you
hit goes into a basket
that we carry over
to the next round.
Chinese melon!
Yeah!
JEFF:
Last shot.
Good round, guys.
Head over
to the slingshot area.
I'll collect your fruit.
Hey, good
work, buddy.
JEFF:
All right, it's a time trial.
Let's have the two slingshotters
come up.
Come on, Gretchen!
Come on, baby,
come on, now!
JEFF:
Here are the rules
for this round:
If you knock the fruit off,
if you break the vase
or if you embed a rock
in the fruit
it goes into the fruit basket.
You have two minutes
to hit as many of the items
as you can.
( cheering )
Yeah!
JEFF:
All right,
round three...
spear throwing,
and this is where
it gets very interesting.
This is
a winner-take-all event.
The single spear
that is closest
to the bull's-eye
when it's over
gets the basket
of fruit
and a very special food source--
a mystery food source.
Who are your two spear throwers?
Step up, mate.
This box is
for shooters only.
You each get
three tosses.
Susan, you're up.
Nice shot!
Come on, Joel,
you can do it.
Come on, Joel.
Nice, Joel!)
Good job!
This is our closest right now.
Pagong.
Nice shot!
( all talking at once )
JEFF:
Those are even right now.
Come on, Joel.
( loud cheering )
Nice!
We want fruit!
New mark to beat.
Come on, Sue.
JEFF:
Last shot, Susan.
Got to get inside that mark.
Nice!
( groaning and cheering )
JEFF:
Victory for Pagong.
Pagong, over here.
Tagi...
stay on your mat.
Nice job, guys--
you get all the fruit...
Yes! Yes!
And a very special
mystery food prize.
Apple?
Oh, A chicken!ars!
Are you kidding? Oh!
( laughing )
Yeah!
Egg-laying chickens...
and all the fruit--
congratulations.
Tagi, sorry.
( chickens clucking )
Don't let them go.
Yeah, that's going to happen.
This is so awesome;
we got chickens.
You guys going to
name these chickens?
Breakfast,
lunch and dinner.
Breakfast, lunch and dinner.
JENNA:
I don't know what brought
us down, but it seems like
winning that challenge just
brought everybody right back up.
I can't speak
for the rest of the tribe,
but I really wanted to win
'cause it was food.
I wanted to win that
more than any
of the other rewards thus far.
Unexpectedly, we came back
with three live chickens
which was absolutely wonderful.
Don't you dare.
Uh...
Whoo!
JENNA:
Aw, Gretchen!
You're so mean.
Mean, my ass.
Well, we're going to see
if they produce any eggs,
but I'm really thinking
that we're going to wait
every other day
and eat a chicken.
GRETCHEN:
They're not going
to be around long.
Everybody's waiting
for them to lay eggs
but I think
they're under a lot of stress
and there's three of them
in that box
and so they have
a very short time to produce
before they're slaughtered.
You could make
a big omelet.
That or we could just make
fried rice with it.
Oh, chicken fried rice?
Chicken fried rice.
Oh, gross! Oh, my God!
JENNA:
Sorry, Breakfast,
Lunch and Dinner.
GERVASE:
The fruit and the chickens
was just so huge
to us, really, I mean...
I think that's the biggest
reward so far to date.
Fresh fruit.
Ooh!
( laughing )
( squeals )
GERVASE:
I think we were down
just because we lost.
I mean, no matter how
you look at it, losing hurts
and we had to vote
somebody off.
So we just had to get out
of that, and then, when we won
the reward challenge, that was
our momentum right there.
SUSAN:
As far as losing
the challenge today,
I was a little irritated.
Here's my dream come true.
I can stomp a guy
on national television
and I miss by two inches.
It was a bummer, but then
when they pulled the chickens
out, I started laughing.
Cutting off a chicken's head?
No, it's not what I would want
to do for food.
I can live without the chicken
right now.
So that was all right.
The other team won some
live chickens with some eggs.
So we came back here
and I went spearfishing
and got us a nice eel.
That's the first eel.
If I'd seen others,
I'd have gotten others.
SUSAN:
Oh, wow.
It's all beautiful meat,
the whole thing.
Nice job, Rich.
Is that pretty?
It's so pretty.
That's a lot of meat, there.
It's all meat.
Beats the hell
out of chicken.
KELLY:
I'd rather eat some eel
than some chicken.
At least we eat stuff
that we go out and catch
and look for ourselves, and
we don't have it handed to us.
It might be a little overcooked.
It's meat.
RICHARD:
Grab a piece.
SUSAN:
Grab a piece and see
if you can rip it apart.
That's what it's
going to take.
RICHARD:
It's cartilaginous,
so chew on it.
SEAN:
The eel was pretty horrible.
Uh, it wasn't any good
whatsoever.
KELLY:
We thought it was
just going to be
you know, big, fat steaks
of meat, but it really wasn't.
RUDY:
I wouldn't go
after eel again
if I had a choice--
I would have rather had
chicken without a doubt.
Wow. That's something.
GRETCHEN:
My feelings
on who the leader is
has always been Greg.
He's just really good at it.
I may be slipping into some sort
of leadership position.
I'm attempting to avoid it.
I don't want to be
the leader of anything.
I go play by myself, help out
the tribe as much as I can
and try and recharge
my batteries
so I can be there fully
with them.
He's really good
at living in the woods, too.
I think, out of everybody here,
Greg's the most comfortable
in the woods.
GREG:
My psychological comfort
does not come
from sleeping with the group
in a hut.
In fact,
they kind of make me nervous,
'cause there are
a lot of people doing
a lot of different things
and it's a lot of energy
in a very small space
while I'm trying to clear
my head of energy.
Sleeping in the forest
is comfortable
for me.
I'm making
a little sleeping pad.
Sleeping pad, sleeping bag--
depending on how big it gets.
I just used some bedding
of debris
or whatever I can find--
palm or the leaves
that are around--
and pile up a bunch of debris.
It's all a nesting instinct.
As with everything,
make yourself a nest.
I nest like a mama bird.
Papa bird-- more like
a papa bird than a mama bird.
A single...
like a bachelor bird, I guess.
Colleen has joined me
in the forest to sleep.
She apparently finds it
more comfortable, as well.
I mean, they go off a lot,
seems like together.
Like last night, for example,
while everybody
was going to bed,
they got out,
and nobody saw them
till just this morning
sometime.
JENNA:
I noticed they seem
to be spending their nights
out under the stars
and cuddling up.
I think it's stepped up
a notch--
maybe a little romance going on.
Um, when we go off,
it's all about sex.
It's all that's happening.
Um...
it's a really passionate
affair right now.
Things are going great.
( laughing )
The question was asked before
whether this was
a romantic situation or not,
and I will reaffirm
that there is no romance.
COLLEEN:
You know,
he reminds me of my friends
back home, so it's like
I can totally, totally
be myself with him.
GREG:
So we like to play together--
not as a romantic situation,
but, yeah
heading back out in the forest
and sleeping out there
and the rest of it is great.
RICHARD:
This is a yellow-banded
sea crate.
We find a number of them
in the jungle.
I haven't seen one
down here on the beach.
I'm hoping
he goes for a swim.
I might help him.
He's awake now.
Oh, I'm not
afraid of snakes.
I mean,
I don't want to be bitten
by something that's deadly,
but, no, I used to play
with garter snakes,
when I was a kid
and feed them frogs, and...
You know, they're not...
They are quick, and it's...
they can move fast,
but you can see
when he's about to coil up
and strike
and you can prepare yourself
and you can get ready to move
before it does.
I want to put him in the water
'cause I want to watch him swim.
We've been told
they're extremely deadly--
immediately deadly,
within six hours deadly.
Horseflies bother me more.
SEAN:
I knew today was going to be
a good day when I woke up.
I haven't had a bowel movement
in nearly two weeks.
This morning, I had my first
bowel movement-- felt fantastic.
( cheering )
I am one
of the bowel movers now.
I'm getting thinner
and thinner.
I think I'm using
most of the rice I make
'cause I'm not bloated
and my pants
are getting skinnier.
Very excited about it--
it's the way
to start the day off, with a
little bit of a bowel movement.
Nice work, Sean.
Go, New York, go.
We were concerned about Dirk
and his eating a while ago,
because he was really
disappearing into nothing.
We're all losing a little
bit of weight,
but Dirk was really losing
a lot of weight.
DIRK:
I definitely lost
a lot of mass,
a lot of muscle mass,
a lot of strength.
It's not going to help me
but, as long as I conserve
my energy--
don't waste it on things
that we don't need--
as long as I'm smart about it,
I think I'll be okay.
KELLY:
We've noticed Dirk kind of
getting a little skinny.
Um, there was a few days
where we were all
kind of concerned about him
and, uh, he was just kind of...
I think, you know, mentally,
he was a little bummed out
and all of us were, like,
"eat more rice, eat more rice."
DIRK:
We're going on
a tapioca hunt.
That way,
you can eat more, Dirk,
'cause you're looking like hell.
You look like a nazi war
prisoner camp, dude.
I don't look that bad.
Yeah, you do.
Nazi war prisoner
camp dude.
Your Adam's apple's about out
to the bottom of your chin.
Yeah. Hell, my arm's.
as big as yours now.
But it was before.
Well, we all kind of try
and keep an eye on him,
'cause he was real skinny
to begin with.
I'm doing the dishes;
I'm going out.
We got that.
Anybody else?
KELLY:
The labor thing,
it's actually better now.
Sean and Dirk
started to realize
that they better, you know,
do something.
Otherwise, they're out of here.
Want me to peel
one of the big ones
when you guys are done?
Is there another knife?
SUSAN:
They've kind of come around
the last couple,
two, three days
and started doing
a little more, but it's
a little too late for that.
Maybe I am on thin ice
with this team now.
I don't know.
I feel like
I'm pulling my weight
and I think
the group sees that
and I'm just going to find
tapioca, and I'm just going
to let it work itself out.
Where you going?
For tapioca?
SEAN:
Yeah.
KELLY:
You know what the,
uh, roots look like.
Yeah, yeah, I just showed Dirk.
SUSAN:
And you know
what the trunks
look like.
Yeah. No, I just showed him
the thing by the raft.
RICHARD:
Kelly, Sue and I--
we need to decide cohesively
who we're going to reject
and it's between Sean and Dirk,
and Sean--
yesterday, he was talking
about how he doesn't want
to form an alliance
because...
Yeah.
You know,
"do unto others" and...
What? You're
"...as others do unto you."
It's just a game;
this is not real life.
So, we're thinking,
"boy, Sean, it's time
for you to go, bud."
Tapioca's good eating, too.
We definitely want a lot of it.
I don't even know if I know
what I'm looking for.
It's a distinctive
reddish root.
Will I know when I find it?
If we look further
along the trail,
maybe we'll have better luck.
I can't find any tapioca, man.
I don't know where it is.
SEAN:
Hermit crab crawling
through the jungle.
Look at the claws
on that thing.
They do make them big
here in the jungle.
What about the tapioca?
They make any tapioca
big in this jungle?
Not really.
We still ain't
found any.
We're sucking at
this jungle thing.
SEAN:
There was about five
on this stem that I picked up
but only one was good.
The rest were mushy.
So I had to throw the rest away.
It wasn't a
complete loss.
I think that we've
exhausted our supply.
So that's the end
of the tapioca, then?
I think. I mean,
you guys have better luck.
You can go look, too.
Rather an unsuccessful
hunt for me and you.
Yep.
Maybe it's
you and me, man.
Maybe we're a bad team.
Probably.
We're a fun team, though.
Got our message.
Check it out.
"Selecting one's
always a chore,
"so check your ego
at the door.
"One to row,
the rest to swim.
Make it fast, and
immunity you'll win."
It's in the water.
We got to win.
KELLY:
Today's day 15
and we have
an Immunity Challenge today.
Hopefully, um, it'll be
something that, uh...
that we can win pretty handily,
and I don't feel like going
to the Immune Council tonight
by any means.
I think we're
all swimming
except one rower.
Gervase can't
swim, and he's
kind of gangly,
so I don't picture him
rowing all that well.
I don't know.
Maybe he can.
I think we certainly
have an edge up.
Apparently, we need one rower
and the rest of us swimming,
which is good, because we have
Kelly who's a rower.
That's what she does
as a profession for a living.
So it's your turn
to shine, Kel.
Oh, boy.
This is it.
You've been waiting
for this.
Your time
to shine.
KELLY:
I'm a commercial
white-water raft guide,
so obviously,
I'm the rower today.
Feeling a little pressure, but
I'm not too worried about it.
I know Gervase can't swim,
so my guess
is that they're going to put him
in the boat rowing,
which is cool for me
because I can beat him
any day of the week.
GERVASE:
"Selecting one
is always a chore
"so check your ego at the door.
"One to row, the rest to swim.
Make it fast,
and immunity you'll win."
The decision that is obvious
is that Gervase should row.
JENNA:
You can look at it
as a disadvantage
that Gervase can't swim.
But we all are going to have
our differences.
Not all of us are going
to be strong at everything.
Wow.
Swimming and rowing.
I sent Gervase to row
so he doesn't have to swim.
But they'll guess that.
They'll know that
that's what we're doing.
Yeah, but I mean,
what other choice do we have?
We might not even get
a life preserver.
"Check your ego
at the door."
Comfort level with swimming's
about 80%.
I mean, I've heard
you're more buoyant
in the ocean,
because of the salt water.
I don't know that, though.
To me, I'll sink
like I was in a pool.
Maybe we have to build something
and the people who swim have
to push it and one guy rows it.
♪ Could be ♪
♪ Who knows? ♪
♪ There's something due
any day ♪
♪ I will know right away ♪
♪ Soon as it shows ♪
♪ It may come cannonballing
down through the sky ♪
♪ Gleam in its eye,
bright as a rose! ♪
♪ The air is humming ♪
♪ And something great
is coming ♪
( humming "Something's Coming" )
I can't wait!
Who knows?!
JEFF:
Today's Immunity Challenge
is called "shipwrecked."
Five members
from each tribe are stranded
on items of floating debris
simulating
a sunken ship disaster.
The remaining two castaways
must rescue
the members of their own tribe
by using outrigger canoes.
Kelly was chosen
to row by Tagi
and Gervase
was chosen by Pagong.
Here's the premise.
It's all on you guys.
You're each going to be
in one of these canoes.
You're going to swim out
to the outside
of your buoy--
yellow and orange.
Once you go
on the outside
of the buoy,
you start heading back
and you start picking up
tribe members.
Once they are on board, though,
they can start helping you
with paddles.
You've got three paddles,
and you've got one bailer,
'cause you
will take on water today,
as rough
as it is.
It's for immunity.
Losing tribe's coming to
Tribal Council tonight.
So what I want to know is,
how did you guys
get selected for this?
Why are you the rower?
Well, I'm a water all-star,
so this is my element
right here,
so there was no choice.
You, on the other hand,
water is...
as we've talked about, this
is a whole new thing for you.
Yes, yes.
Are you rowing
because you'd
rather row
than swim?
I think that's what we
were thinking at first,
but I knew it would be
something kind of tricky
and it's show time,
so I like the spotlight.
Really? Lot of pressure.
Pressure's good.
They're doing
nothing out there.
It is all
the person on the boat.
All right. Good luck.
Thank you.
For the idol, get in your boats.
Survivors ready?
Go!
( paddle splashing )
( paddles splashing )
( all shouting )
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Over here.
Over this way.
Over to the right.
Get it up here!
( all cheering )
( cheering )
JEFF:
Gervase's
last words were,
"I like the spotlight.
Bring it on."
Who's invincible
tonight?
Gervase!
Does anybody
feel especially
invincible tonight?
I got beat by a guy
who can't even swim.
Yeah, but he
wasn't swimming.
Yeah.
Go, Kelly.
I can't
believe that
I lost that.
Hey, guys,
the immunity idol.
Welcome back home,
immunity idol!
KELLY:
Tonight we have to take
the suckfest hike
to the Tribal Council,
and we get to vote somebody off
tonight, unfortunately.
You know, despite everything,
I was the best choice
to put in that boat today,
and, you know, like I said,
sometimes your best
just isn't good enough
and life just wouldn't be life
if everybody didn't get
their little embarrassments
from time to time, so...
That which doesn't
kill you
makes you stronger,
right, Sean?
Absolutely.
I say that to myself
all the time.
Me, too.
Same exact sentence.
Oh, yeah, it's always
in the back of my mind
whether or not
anyone's going to vote
against me.
I don't have a vote
against me yet,
and now we're losing numbers
so I'm sure one's coming,
just like the other people
who don't have a vote
against them, one's coming
in their direction, too.
I suspect it might be Rudy.
That's how I'll probably cast
my vote at this point.
I'm ready.
RICHARD:
It's an interesting game,
but it's a game,
and I've had
a strategy from day one.
I've already built an alliance
and we're going to work through
as best we can right to the end
before the free-for-all.
Just walking to our death
right here.
DIRK:
I think I'm vulnerable.
I've tried my hardest
and put as much effort
if not more into everything,
but I haven't been successful
in any areas so maybe some
people will look at that
and say,
"Dirk doesn't know
what he's doing.
He's being lazy." Whatever.
But I think they realize that
I'm a valuable member
of this team, so I'm not
worried about being voted off.
I think I'll be here tomorrow.
Ready?
What's to say?
Tribal council.
Tough situation.
Kelly, tell me about morale.
Two tough losses back-to-back.
Personally, for me,
today was really hard.
Um... coulda, shoulda, woulda
a lot of things, you know?
I said some things
at the beach... whatever.
I'm not making excuses,
not trying to,
not going to, you know?
I gave it my best today
and just wasn't good enough,
so ate a little crow,
it's all right.
Doesn't mean I
have to like it.
Sean, your role here?
Very nebulous.
I don't know
what I'm doing here.
After how long we been here?
15, 16 days.
I still haven't found my niche.
I'm just here
to have fun.
I'll take it as far
as I can go
till you throw me kicking
and screaming off this island.
Dirk?
It seems like
I've noticed
you spending
more time alone.
How much of that time
do you spend thinking
about how effective you are
at fitting in this group?
I'd say very little.
I can't think myself into being
more effective, you know?
I'm working hard.
I'm catching fish
and I've been completely
unsuccessful.
I'm working hard
at hunting tapioca
and I've been completely
unsuccessful.
I've been working ha...
You know, it's like I've failed
at everything I've tried,
but it's not like
the effort's not there,
you know what
I'm saying?
Richard?n.
15 days now together,
inevitable that certain
alliances, even within a group,
smaller factions begin
to develop.
Have you guys
reached a point now
where you have
this tight unit
that these alliances are going
to come in to play in the vote?
The alliances that you talk
about, the Rudy and I
and the Sean and Dirk
kind of hanging,
and the Sue and Kelly together,
are almost kind of little teams
within a team doing things
'cause it usually takes
a couple of people to do things.
I think a bigger alliance is
what all six of us have created
so I don't think that
the smaller ones detract
from how we feel about
the six of...
all of us together.
It's time to vote.
Dirk.
I love you, but I just can't
stand the complaining.
For the first time,
I'm voting for Rudy,
only because this is
probably an athletic competition
coming up
that we're going
to have to win
and that's the only reason
I would cast a vote against him.
He's a phenomenal person.
Fire represents life
on the island.
Your torches represent
your identity here.
Directly across from you are
four torches that represent
the first four people
that have been voted
off the island.
Tonight, a fifth torch
will be added to that group.
I'll go tally the votes.
Before I read the votes,
I just want to remind you
once they're tallied,
the decision is final
and the person must
leave the island immediately.
I'll read
the votes.
First vote...
"Dirk."
"Sue."
"Rudy."
"Dirk."
That's two
votes for Dirk.
"Dirk."
That's three votes.
We don't need to
read the last one.
The tribe
has spoken.
It's time for
you to go.
All right.
Guys, good luck.
You can take your torches
and head back to camp.
Good night.
( primal singing )
JEFF:
Next week, on Survivor--
at Tagi,
Rich goes native.
Who cares?
JEFF:
Over at Pagong,
Gervase ruffles some feathers
with a sexist remark.
Girls are the stupidest thing
on the planet next to cows.
It's a fact, though.
Oh, I beg to differ.
GRETCHEN:
So, I told those girls,
when they write your name
on that piece of paper,
and look straight into the lens
and go, "moo."
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and SURVIVOR PRODUCTIONS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
I guess I want to start
by just thanking the Lord
just for this
unbelievable blessing.
I mean, this whole thing
has just been one wild trip.
He had 15 days planned
for me on this island.
I believe I kicked it
as hard as I could.
Completely surprised
to be taken out this early
and I thank the Lord
for that,
'cause I know
he's got a plan
for me to move on
somewhere else.