JEFF PROBST:
16 Americans,
marooned for 39 days
in the middle
of the South China Sea.
Separated into two tribes--
Tagi and Pagong--
they competed against each
other to remain on the island,
but now the tribes
have merged into one.
Rattana is the name,
and it is everyone
for themselves.
Every third night,
the entire tribe will hike
deep into the jungle
to take part
in the Tribal Council,
where they must vote
one of their own
off the island.
In the end, one will remain
and will leave the island
with $1 million in cash.
Last week on Survivor:
The stakes were raised
for the castaways
as the two tribes
merged into one.
GREG:
There was a lot of baggage
that we left
on that Pagong beach.
JEFF:
The members of Pagong
were upbeat
as they paddled to their
new home at Tagi beach.
I'm excited to go to their camp
and meet new people.
Rich came out and was, like,
"Hey, how are you?"
You know, he swam out,
which was really nice.
They welcomed us with open arms.
JEFF:
But the Tagi alliance
was a wolf in sheep's clothing.
I don't need to
deal with that.
After Gretch?
Jenna.
I was thinking Sean.
JEFF:
Rudy wasn't happy
with the new Rattana Tribe.
RUDY:
All of a sudden,
we doubled our population.
Personally,
it's a pain in the ass.
JEFF:
Greg won the first
immunity talisman,
ensuring that only he could not
be voted off at Tribal Council.
Sean began
his alphabet voting strategy
and to the surprise of many,
it was Gretchen who was ousted.
Oh, my God.
It's me.
JEFF:
Nine members of Rattana
are left.
Tonight, one more will go.
SEAN:
Today is, like, Day 22.
We had a vote last night,
which is always pretty beat.
Always puts us
in a pretty somber mood.
But last night was
a very strange vote.
Last night, it looks
like there was a conspiracy,
and maybe I'm being paranoid
and I didn't want to believe it,
but four people from Tagi
voted for Gretchen, I think.
SEAN:
You know, the bloodbath
has begun, you know.
People have started taking it
a different way,
'cause there's really no good
reason other than strategy
to vote Gretchen off.
GREG:
Gretchen distinctly disliked
this part of the game.
This was her hardest thing
was voting people off,
and the part
that she liked the most
was the survival aspect.
GERVASE:
I really don't know
what happened last night.
At first sight, it looks like
they just picked Gretchen off.
SEAN:
I think that
my former team, Tagi,
probably formed an alliance
against what they perceived
as her... as their
strongest member of Pagong,
which was Gretchen.
It was my idea to get rid
of Gretchen because I...
I thought that she was going
to be the next leader.
She had to go because she...
is bright and, uh, is strong
and she was a threat.
SEAN:
The, uh, duplicity of the whole
thing is pretty bad,
because I think that people
went out of their way
to befriend her, and, uh...
and those were the people who
subsequently voted against her.
GREG:
That's the game--
duplicitous, sleaziness--
if you want to play that way.
KELLY:
This is a game;
don't take it personally.
You know, if people came here
to make, you know,
bosom buddies
and, you know, lifelong friends,
they should've gone
to summer camp.
GERVASE:
I think, really,
if it happens again,
then you can say for sure
there's an alliance,
but if it does,
I'm more determined than ever
to bust that plan up and still
kill them all and win, you know.
As far as Pagong,
we are now four.
They are now five.
They do have a voting bloc
on us whether we see it or not
and they can pick us off
one by one.
Who needs men?
My best strategy
is to bond with the women
and try to hold on to the
women's vote as long as I can.
I'm so excited, guys.
I don't care if you
vote me off now
'cause I made it
to my cutoff point.
The girls... no,
there ain't no girls
going for a while,
you guys.
Thanks, Sue.
That makes me
feel better.
SUSAN:
The women seem
to be getting along well
because the women
are all workers.
Actually, I like Jenna better
than I thought I would.
I thought she would drive me
wild and she doesn't, so...
Don't worry.
The guys' days
are numbered.
They are numbered.
Us girls... us girls are
here for a while, trust me.
Oh, man, I love it.
We'll be up at the end.
I do see the women versus men
vote continuing on in Rattana.
As far as my three votes, top--
they're all men.
Oh, God, you guys,
look at these crabs.
I see women go out,
get the crab traps.
The women fix the hut.
We're carrying the weight
of the team.
Maybe that's unfair,
but that's how I see it.
Ooh, look at it.
( women screaming )
Get him...
get him, Sue.
Beat him
with the shoe.
( women laughing )
She had me beat the
hell out of a crab
with a shoe.
SUSAN:
As far as the women
becoming an alliance,
there's a chance that the girls
might want to have an alliance
after there's a few more guys
knocked off.
If they do,
I'll just lead on with them
like,
"Yeah, that's a good idea."
But as far as the women
forming an alliance
and making one, no.
It ain't gonna happen.
I already got mine.
I like mine.
KELLY:
We're all hungry
and we're low on energy,
and there's still no one else
providing any food
except for Rich.
And we're having
to ration the rice.
You don't have
to put
both bowls on right now, Rudy,
is what
I'm saying.
Don't be
stubborn.
RUDY:
I ain't stubborn.
I'm going to eat
if everybody's
going to eat.
Okay, okay.
I ain't above eating.
Having nine people,
it's, uh...
everything gets smaller again.
The rice pot got smaller,
the sleeping quarters
got smaller.
We got four,
five bags...
So it's four bags there,
so we got eight meals there
so that's four days.
Or, no, that's only two days.
So, a can's only going
to last us two days?
We're eating that much.
We have to ration
it, then.
So instead of making
three pots tonight
we should make two pots
twice a day.
RUDY:
When we go
over there to eat,
the majority rules.
Yeah, two pots.
SUSAN:
I wish some of the other people
would start conserving
a little more...
people that are being pigs.
I'll only eat one bowl
at a sitting.
I'm planning on staying
until the end,
so I really want
to have something
for the last couple of days.
We have our fisherman;
it's Rich.
That's Rich's job.
Oh, wow. Two?
Four.
Four?
( laughing ):
What a catch.
A ray, a parrot fish,
a catfish
and a nice little nurse shark.
Baby's gonna have
some protein today.
GERVASE:
Greg showing up, going out
trying to spear a fish.
They've got nothing.
I'm not going to do
any better than they will.
And I think Rich
is in a great position.
We vote Rich off,
we don't eat.
Get the torches going.
Get everything
happening.
This is big time,
guys.
Rich, Rich, Rich,
Rich, Rich!
RICHARD:
Now, which one of
you sons of bitches
wrote my name
on a card
last night?
( laughing )
The bastard didn't get
a fish.
Yeah, he's out of here.
I'm starving.
RICHARD:
As far as who voted for me
at the Tribal Council
last night...
and I'm not certain who it is.
I'm thinking
it was probably Greg
who felt threatened by me.
But it could have been
any of them.
I've only been with them
a day or two
and I'd not brought in
any fish.
Today, on the other hand
I brought in a huge catch.
Three rays...
They just lapped that up.
That one's
pretty meaty.
GREG:
Let's make
them dead
so they can
stop suffocating.
( loud smack )
Aah!
You guys, I mean,
there's no other
humane way
to do that?
It seems humane to me.
Right through its brain.
I could eat rice
for 17 more days.
the whole time,
but they're loving the fish
and it seems to make people
feel great,
and I squeeze every ounce
of credit out of it that I can.
Susie-Q, look at that, please.
I know,
I said
they look
beautiful.
Dang, Rich!
Those rays
look really good.
We're all very proud
of you, Richie.
It's the most fish
we've had.
Good.
Watch Susie perk up.
She just gets a little protein
and she's back in the race.
GREG:
Rich is playing a big game.
I think Rich thinks
he's very clever.
He has a lot of things
going on in his mind
that he, uh...
selectively decides
what he will share
and with whom.
Fear... comes from...
That's right.
It's useless.
I think religion
is what destroys
our society.
Whoa!
I think it's the reason
people treat
other people as if
they're lower
than themselves.
Rich, that's
ground-shaking.
RICHARD:
I'm not sure
how Greg sees me.
I'm trying to figure out
whether or not
he's trying to build
an alliance or pull me in
or make me like him in some way.
GREG:
It's kind of weird.
It's good and bad.
You should
give it a go.
RICHARD:
Thank you, buddy.
Don't get that
stuff near me
with those funny faces.
JENNA:
I'm seeing Greg
in a more devious way
than I've ever seen him before.
Since we moved,
I saw him change so much,
and so transparently,
to me anyway,
that I've changed
my whole attitude towards Greg.
GREG:
This scheme is interesting
in that you make friends
with people,
you make alliances
and you have to
cut them loose at some point.
JENNA:
Greg is working just about
everybody in the group.
I think he's always had Colleen
wrapped around
his little finger.
It's not like that.
I mean, honestly,
if there was a girl here
who I got along with
really, really well,
it would be the same thing
that way.
I feel
like I have a friend
and I have somebody
who's my equal
that I can actually
have a conversation with.
Yesterday
night...
I'm voting for you next time.
Fine. See
what happens.
You're voting
for me.
GREG:
This is the game.
You bring
this little kitty along.
You have your little kitten,
and you pet your kitten
and you enjoy this kitten
and the kitten sleeps with you
every night
and then, you're hungry, man.
You look right
in the kitten's eye
and snap its neck.
It's nothing personal.
You're hungry.
The kitten has to give its life
for the next level.
What is it about your pet cat?
My pet
kitten?
Your pet kitten.
It's you,
kitty.
KELLY:
I see him as being a chameleon.
Changing his colors to fit
whoever he's around.
RICHARD:
He's certainly interacted
with me
in an incredibly
interesting way
that suggests to me
that he's trying something
that I'm very, very wary of
and that's great.
JENNA:
Rich finds Greg attractive,
so Rich throws these
little innuendoes out there
and Greg will just pick right up
on them,
sit right real close to Rich
and he's playing him.
Orgy, Greg?
Orgy?
Sure.
Have...
You have?
Oh, not right now?
He thought it was
an offer.
GERVASE:
Greg and Rich have joked around
a lot.
We were talking one night.
Rich was getting real personal
about his business,
and Greg was all in it.
You guys have never been
with another guy?
No.
Greg has.
I mean...
Rich, seriously?
Just kid... kid stuff.
That's what
freaks me out.
I mean...
well...
No, I...
You...
GREG:
I think, uh, Rich likes
to flirt with everybody,
and instead of directly
shutting him down,
I only played his game back.
He's the shy one
on tape.
I didn't expect that.
I'll tell you the story later.
RICHARD:
He's manipulative.
He's trying to win me over
in some way.
He's just not going about it in
bright enough a way for me.
I would like to spend more time
with him and get to know him,
but... I would also rather have
the million dollars
than to have somebody
like him around to worry about.
Oh, gee.
What the hell is that?
Oh, boy.
Oh, no way.
"It takes skill
to carve the arc.
"May your aim be true
and find its mark.
"Archery is the sport of kings.
A reward from home is
what victory brings."
Oh, my, my.
I'm never going
to win anything
( laughing ):
around here.
Got a little bit
Bows and arrows.
SEAN:
You know, if it has
anything to do
with something from home,
I'd like Jenna
to win it.
Thank you, Sean.
I hope it's
my pictures.
They might have
our family send
a care package...
everybody.
They'll just give you
the care package...
KELLY:
The reward is going
to be something from home
and, um, Jenna's thinking
it's-it's our pictures
that we got to bring, and, like,
she really, really...
She misses her daughters
terribly.
Aren't you excited?
I love this stuff.
I'm going to go home
and be, like,
"Oh, I got to do bows
and arrows."
SUSAN:
Wow.
Okay, Jenna,
Too high.
Is that how you hold it?
( laughing ):
Oh.
SUSAN:
It's guys against girls, too,
'cause this
is very even
because these
bow and arrows...
and these
arrows are...
none of them are straight.
Go, Kelly.
Keep your
finger over it.
Okay, put the
string up.
Now, pull her.
Even if you want to
keep it at a angle.
Nice, Rudy.
Who's on the boat?
I think it's Jeff.
RICHARD:
Bringing news
of the competition, I bet.
Oh, hi, Jeff.
It better be something
really good.
I'd rather have food
than anything
from home right now.
I would so much
rather have food.
It probably is
a refrigerator,
but what are we going
to refrigerate, our rice?
Maybe it's got
food already.
It's ice cream
sandwiches.
Okay.
( chuckles )
Move the crate.
Perfect.
Oh... a TV.
Okay, now, before
we begin today's
reward challenge,
I'm going to show you
some short clips of video
sent from home.
The winner
of the archery
contest gets
to watch their
entire video.
With that...
I give you this,
a little something from home.
Okay, "a little something
from home."
That's cool.
Hi, Dad.
Um, I hope you're doing
very well.
That's my kid.
Aw...
I'm doing pretty well.
Um... I hope
you come back with the million.
Uh, like I said in my letter,
I just...
I just wish you lots of luck.
Yay.
( laughing )
That's sweet.
RICHARD:
Yeah,
that's really cool.
It is cool.
Okay.
Hi, Kelly.
Hi.
I hope you're doing good.
You'll probably win,
but I miss you anyway.
I'm ready for you to come home.
So, eat your rice, keep smiling
and, uh, come home
and let's go kayaking.
I'm ready to go.
Peace.
( laughing )
I don't know.
Maybe everybody in the room,
anybody who's watching this
right now
could just join in.
You make mama real proud.
Don't go shaming the family,
sleeping with everybody
on the island.
Just remember who loves you.
Sis-sis...
and she's thinking of you.
Mmm-mmm-mmm.
( laughing )
Oh, good, good.
All right.
I'm doing this off the top
of my head, so...
That's my husband
holding my dog.
Aw...
That's my dog.
You are me, I am you
and you are me.
Together, we make it
through eternity.
Not bad, eh?
You know, here's Stimpy.
He's going to come up
and give you a big kiss.
Here he comes.
( imitating airplane engine )
( grunting )
( laughing )
Oh, my God.
SUSAN:
Oh...
my dog looks so unimpressed.
Missing you?
SUSAN:
Oh, yeah, she is.
BOTH:
Hi, Colleen.
We love you.
SUSAN:
Aw...
COLLEEN:
That's my cat.
( laughing )
This is our
sign-off now.
Have fun.
MOTHER:
Good luck.
That was so cute.
They're really cute.
Hi, Rudy.
I bet you're surprised
to see me
on the island with you.
45 Years.
Just wanted to let you know
how much we missed you.
Look at Grandpa.
Hey, who is that?
( granddaughter gurgling )
And whether you win or not,
I'm proud of you
for having been selected.
I hope
you're enjoying yourself
'cause I know you like
the challenge.
Take care.
I love you very much.
JEFF:
That's a love letter.
Yeah.
All right.
It was nice.
SEAN:
Aw, there's my sister.
Yeah, that's the...
We call that the blue bomb.
( crash )
WOMAN:
You think he'll notice?
ALL:
We miss you, Sean.
Come home soon...
but not too soon.
Good luck.
Aw.
That was nice.
Hi, Daddy.
Baby!
Oh, look.
Oh, she's beautiful.
Tell Daddy.
Who's the man?
Daddy!
Oh, she's so cute.
Do it real loud.
Wha-zup!
Say, bye-bye, Daddy.
Bye-bye, Daddy.
Bye-bye, baby.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
that's cute.
Not too bad.
Oh, she's beautiful.
That's my heart and my soul,
everything right there.
Mom's beautiful, too.
You shouldn't have
shown me that, man.
JEFF:
Well, it breaks
my heart
to say this,
Jenna.
Oh, don't tell me.
We never received
a tape back.
And I'm really sorry.
Oh, man.
Are we going to do
the archery now?
JEFF:
Well, there is
an upside to this
that still
includes you.
The reward for
today's challenge
is two parts.
One is a private screening
for the full tape.
The winner also gets to make
their own video postcard
and send it home.
And that one, Jenna,
I can guarantee you
will get there
'cause I'll put it
in the overnight
myself tomorrow.
So, one person's going to get
the whole kit and caboodle
tonight
and the others are going
to get nothing else.
Okay, so you're going
to get one arrow,
that's it.
Remember, the
one who shoots
their arrow
closest to the bull's-eye,
gets to see
their entire video
and make one
of their own.
You guys
comfortable?
Nice.
Greg is on the mark.
I'll let you handle this.
The split...
Yeah, I'm
worried about that.
Good try.
Yay. You hit
the board.
Oh, I wanted
to see my daughters.
Go, Rudy.
Make it count.
Well, this ain't my bag.
JEFF:
Greg's still looking
good right now.
Close...
but no cigar.
Come on, Sue.
You guys...
JEFF:
Tim's waiting
to hear.
Waiting to hear
from you.
Well... not close.
Good luck, Kelly.
Good try.
Great try.
Nice try.
Mom and Dad
would love
to hear from
you, Colleen.
Good velocity.
All right, Gervase,
no big deal.
Come on, for
your little girl.
The entire...
Nice try,
Gervase. Nice try.
Okay, Rich.
Let's go, Richie.
Dead-Eye Rich.
Here he goes.
Last shot.
It's up to you.
No.
Congratulations, man.
Wait a minute.
Congratulations, Greg.
Thanks, guys.
JEFF:
So Greg is going
back up there
and watch his tape.
You can include
these guys if you want.
You can do whatever
you want with it.
Of course.
If it's going to be funny,
which I figured it would,
I thought other people might
get a kick out of it.
At least she could provide
entertainment for other people.
Mukaluka, mau-mau, ping-ping.
( clicking tongue )
How are you doing?
I miss you very much.
( kissing sounds )
That's right, ping-ping.
RICHARD:
I didn't think Greg's tape
was unusual.
I expected that
and was excited by it.
You could tell
she was having fun
and knew he would laugh
at what she was doing
and I was laughing.
I loved it.
Any circumstance
you find yourself in,
you're not sure what to do--
you're in a quandary;
you're in a pickle;
you're in a bind;
think what Billy Joel would do.
Think about it.
( laughing )
Think, what would Billy Joel do?
Anything.
Let's talk about
who's probably
sleeping on the island
right now.
All the giant,
scary spiders are sleeping.
That's how mom used to put us
to sleep at night.
All the animals are sleeping.
You make Mom proud.
You make Mom real proud.
Just remember who loves you.
Sis-sis.
( kissing sounds )
( silly grunting )
SEAN:
I definitely see Greg
differently now
after seeing his video
and attaching a lit bit
of a family with him.
At least we know
he's not the only screwball
in his family.
Maybe it's a genetic trait
over there.
Okay.e on, buddy.
Hi, Julie.
I just want to say,
you know,
it was really special
for you to send me
and everybody here
what you did.
We feel like we could feel you
and we felt you.
Some of us felt you
and others just imagined
what it's like to feel you.
RUDY:
I can't understand a guy
talking to his sister that way.
It sounded like Greg
was talking, maybe, incest.
That's the way it sounded to me.
( laughing )
Why not make allusions?
It crosses all those borders.
And, God, what are people
going to think?
And then, sexual allusions
for my sister?
What's gonna happen?
Julie, we got to put up with
this for about two more weeks
and, uh, then we
might kill him.
Is that doing
you a favor?
( laughing )
Good work, Rudy.
Good job, Rudy.
RUDY:
Yeah.
JENNA:
I can't imagine
anybody missing their kids
more than I do every night.
Miss my beauties.
Miss Sadie and Sabrina.
I can't imagine my mom
not getting the tape out.
It would've done wonders
to see that my kids are okay.
To hear their voices.
To hear, "I love you, Mommy."
RICHARD:
Yesterday was cool.
We had that reward challenge
with the bow and arrow
and the reward was, the, uh...
videotapes from home,
and for me,
that was way better than food.
GERVASE:
Now, seeing those videos of
everybody's family, it's, like,
even if you didn't
like somebody before,
you see that somebody
cares and loves this person,
so it makes it harder for me
to boot somebody off now.
KELLY:
I felt so bad for Jenna.
She practiced all morning
on that stupid bow and arrow
and then it was just, like,
"Why bother" for her.
Those are my bruises
from the bow and arrow.
This is from the bow and arrow.
GREG:
I don't know
what her feeling is
because now it seems like
she wants to leave the island
and see her girls.
This is going to make it
that much easier
when I do get kicked off.
I'm going to probably cry,
but you know what?
Then I'm going to get off
and go...
"What an adventure!"
And then I get to go home
to my kids, so...
GERVASE:
Jenna is a threat to me
because she has kids
and I have kids, so we're,
like, single parents,
and if people feel
for single parents
and she's tugging on
people's emotions right there
and that can sway somebody
not to vote for Jenna,
and that's a threat for me.
Gervase? I don't see him
doing very much.
SUSAN:
The fact you have
more people here now
and we're having to forage
for more food
and there's a lot more slackers
on this other team.
SUSAN:
Gervase. He's a nice guy.
I don't like feed...
I don't like feeding
people like that,
though, you know
whaYeah.ean?
That's where I'm...
That's where I'm
coming from now.
GERVASE:
My work philosophy is this:
Rich is, like,
the resident fisherman;
Rudy's the cook;
Sean is hauling in wood
every day--
you know, it seems like
everybody has a role here--
and I'm just sitting back
relaxing.
Watch me-- I'm going to work
that boy till he's gone now.
He bugs me.
GREG:
Gervase is honest.
He's not playing
anybody else's game.
I've said over and over
that he was an example
for people
thrown out of their element
to really succeed and have
a great time, which Gervase has.
I got a king.
( laughing )
GERVASE:
How have I survived this long?
I always said when I came here,
I was going to be
the entertainer.
The cards man--
I'm glad you brought them.
It adds a new dimension
to island life.
GERVASE:
I'm not trying to do anything
shifty or shady;
I'm just being me
and people like me
because that's who I am.
Gervase is not that charming,
trust me.
He's a slacker,
so he won't be around long.
Hey.
"Pull me."
Oh, look at this.
"If you want to win immunity
"at the next challenge,
just slip onto the right rope
and run."
"Beware of dead ends.
"The prize you seek...
"is waiting...
at the end of the line."
Wow, that
sounds hard.
A significant amount of luck
with this one.
Oh, you've got
to love that.
At least this way,
I have a chance.
JEFF:
Day 24 on the island.
Since the merger,
nothing has been more important
than voting strategy.
The gears are churning.
Nobody is safe.
The only way to stay
in this game:
win today's immunity challenge.
JEFF:
Here we are--
immunity time... again.
"Into the Line" is a rope course
designed to be confusing.
It's a jungle rope maze with
five checkpoints along the way.
Your job is to collect
the colored carabineers
at every checkpoint.
Here's the only hiccup:
you have to be attached
to the rope course at all times
with your carabineer
you have two of them.
At certain points, you're going
to come to a junction--
these trees.
You can't get past them.
You have to take your
other carabineer,
reattach...
then you can un-attach...
now spin around, maneuver,
however you want to do it.
The only thing
you have to keep in mind
is one of these
has to be on at all times.
Also at each checkpoint
are several ropes
that lead directly
to the next checkpoint,
but several ropes
lead to dead ends.
If you hit a dead end,
you've got to backtrack
to your last checkpoint
and choose a new line.
The first person
to reach the end of the course
with five carabineers
gets immunity.
The tighter, the better?
Survivors, ready...
go!
What's happened to us?
We're idiots!
Oh, dude.
( cheering )
Wow! work, man.
Congratulations.
Give me five!
Very good. Very good.
Yes!
Well earned.
KELLY:
I knew coming here that
we'd have to vote people off.
What I didn't bank on
was the feelings
that you'd have
towards these people.
I feel like I feel
every Tribal Council
only it gets worse
every time.
I feel like a backstabber.
I feel like a liar.
God, some people
are so nervous, it's sick.
It's sick how nervous
some people are.
RUDY:
People are all looking
around a little more
because it's starting
to get down to the wire,
and evidently,
we're the only ones
with a plan right now.
Once it's past the
next council,
we're invincible.
Right now we're
not invincible.
The voting now
should get very interesting.
If people are fear- and
self-preservation motivated,
they'll band together.
They'll form alliances.
They'll start beating
people out.
Fear-motivated
self-preservation
is the worst game
I can imagine.
KELLY:
How do you, you know,
stay true to yourself
and maintain integrity
and still play this game?
And you know what? You can't.
Yeah, I think that
would look better.
Yeah, tell Rudy that.
RUDY:
It's cut and dried that we can
eliminate somebody every time,
and if we don't,
I'll have to break
somebody's kneecap or something.
SUSAN:
So as long as everybody
can keep their mouth shut now.
Kelly's a little freaky.
She's gets a little going.
I'm like, "Just shut up.
Just vote this, and shut up."
KELLY:
I keep telling myself
"Well, I have enough friends.
I didn't come here
to make friends," and da-da-da.
And the truth is,
I like these people.
GERVASE:
This is a game.
You're allowed to do this.
Alliances are fair game.
My thing is, we should always
have the upper hand.
We should've voted Rudy...
We should have voted
for Rudy at first
and then, next vote,
vote your conscience.
Always keep the upper hand
because if they try something,
you can stop it.
SUSAN:
As far as there being
a counterstrategy
from the other side, yeah,
there is some fear about that
because we haven't got
enough of them voted off yet.
COLLEEN:
We have
the upper hand right now, easy.
We have four people
that we could come together
have a vote, and get
the next person off.
Welcome to Tribal Council
number eight.
You guys are now
the final core group of nine.
Two of you will make it,
survive long enough to get
to the final vote.
The other seven of you
will return to be
the jury that delivers
that vote, so no matter
who gets voted off,
from this point forward,
when they get voted off,
we'll all be back here
in 15 days to determine
who leaves with $1 million.
So, Richard,
bearing that in mind,
how do you balance
the ruthlessness
required to get
to the final two
with the likability needed
to get the final vote?
Good question.
I'm not even exactly sure
what my strategy's going to be
as to who I'm going to vote for
from week to week.
I'm just going
to keep getting fish,
feeding people--
hope they're happy.
How about
you, Gervase?
You're wearing immunity;
tonight you're fine.
Same thing applies to you.
How do you find that balance?
Just... I'm winging it.
Every day out here,
I'm just winging it.
I like everybody here, you know,
and after seeing their videos
of their families,
I can put faces
with them now.
I see they have
loved ones like I do
caring about them,
rooting for them,
so it makes it a lot harder.
Jenna, how surprised
were you last week
to see Gretchen
get voted off?
I was very surprised.
I would've thought she would
have made it to the final two,
but when we merged,
strategies had to shift
and it looked like they
were getting rid of leaders,
so, from here on out,
if I get voted off,
I'll wear it
like a badge of honor
when I walk
down there.
Susan, straight up,
is there an alliance?
No, not that I...
I vote people off
that I don't care for,
you know, that really would
irritate me if I was
working with them at a job
or something like that.
Here, I got a chance
to vote them off.
I can get rid of them.
It's, like, yeah!
Kelly, same question.
Do I have to answer?
I'm just kidding.
Has your voting strategy changed
now or will it change tonight?
I vote for who I don't
particularly like.
I vote for who I don't want
to spend the next 15 days with.
Colleen, would you do
whatever it takes
to get this money?
Would you play sides
against each other?
No.
Just not important
enough?
Right.
What brought you here
if it's not the money?
I mean, I'm here
for the money, too.
I mean, give me a break.
Of course.
But the thing is that
everybody's here for the money,
you know?
I'm not going to listen
to everybody's sob stories
and then weigh them.
That's ridiculous.
Everybody wants the money.
All right. Gervase?
It's time to vote.
My vote is for Jenna.
I think she's really missing
her kids now.
She didn't get
the videotape.
There's not a letter for her,
so, you know, I think
it's really hurting her,
so this is her ticket.
Keeping with my strategy
of alphabetical order,
I'm voting for Greg tonight.
It would have been
Gervase's turn, but he won
immunity, so I had to skip him.
Next person in order is Greg.
I don't think this vote is
going to mean very much.
First time for paranoia,
second time for irritation
and third time because
my ear infection is clearing up.
Good night, sweetheart,
yeah, it's time to go.
No more competition.
Talk to you later, Greg.
Bye-bye.
As always I'd like to remind you
that once the votes are tallied,
the decision is final
and the person will be asked
to leave the island immediately.
I'll read the votes.
"Jenna."
"Greg."
Three votes for Greg,
three votes for Jenna.
"Greg."
No!
( mock sobbing )
JEFF:
Take care, Greg.
That's all I need.
Bye, everyone.
Greg, the tribe
has spoken.
It's time
for you to go.
Bye, everybody.
( sobbing )
( laughter )
RUDY:
I believed him
for a minute.
RICHARD:
You believed him, Rudy?
For a minute there.
When the tears fell.
Look at the tears
back there.
That's it
for tonight's Tribal Council.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Good night.
Next week on Survivor:
I'm just being honest.
If you can't take
the honesty...
Cracks begin to appear
in the alliance.
I'm hoping that Kelly hasn't
joined forces
with somebody else.
Someone will win a letter
in the reward challenge.
Will Jenna finally hear
from her children?
JENNA:
I want the letter from home.
I haven't seen or heard
anything from my kids.
A twist of fate
that maybe some
didn't expect
and some... well...
some did.
An excellent game,
well manufactured.
I harbor no resentment
for any of you
who voted for me,
against me or otherwise.
I feel like it's
probably a pretty
darn good time.
Thanks, guys.