JEFF PROBST:
16 Americans forced
to abandon ship
in the middle
of the South China Sea.
Marooned for 39 days,
they must work together
to build shelter,
find food,
and survive the island.
But ultimately, it is
everyone for themselves.
Every third night they will
hike deep into the jungle
to take part
in the Tribal Council
where they must vote one
of their own off the island.
In the end,
only one will remain
and will leave the island
with $1 million in cash.
Last week on Survivor
the two tribes arrived
at separate beaches
and began building
their new home.
( whooping )
On Pagong Beach, trouble began
when B.B. tried to force
his work ethic on the tribe.
B.B.:
We got a lot of lazy people
if you want to know the truth.
JOEL:
He's a character, man.
I don't think he likes me much.
We can't have lazy people.
JEFF:
Over at Tagi Beach,
the generation gap
was also causing problems.
KELLY:
He was yelling at everybody.
He may be 72 years old
and an ex-Navy Seal,
but that doesn't mean
that this is his world.
I don't even know
what "MTV" means, you know.
I got to fit in, not them.
You know, there's more of them
than there is of me.
JEFF:
And Stacey, the attorney,
attempted to organize
the women against Rudy.
STACEY:
Kelly and I get along real well
and we've been talking
about who
would be best to vote off.
We've talked to Sue about it.
SUSAN:
She don't like Rudy
because he's too barky.
Anybody's too barky
and too bossy for Stacey
because she
doesn't move her ass.
The chicks think I'm voting
for one person and I'm not.
What time do we
got to do this at?
We've got
the Tribal Council tonight
and one of us is going to leave.
RICHARD:
I've narrowed it down to four.
I'm one of them.
First person voted
off the island...
Sonja.
The tribe has spoken.
Although likable and sweet,
Sonja was considered
the weakest link in the tribe
and was first to go.
15 are left.
Who will be going home
this week?
STACEY:
I'm hungry.
I think we're
all pretty hungry.
I've gone days when I've only
had some fruit, but...
there's no prospect of having
any fruit here. It's worse.
We got two rats,
primed and ready to be cooked.
It's dire.
RUDY:
These guys were talking
about eating a rat.
And when I get hungry enough,
I'll eat one, but not now.
I'm not close to it yet.
SEAN:
I'd like to catch something
and eat something of our own,
and not have it be a rat.
I'd like that a lot.
KELLY:
Fishing, um...
I think we've been doing,
you know,
w-what we're supposed to do.
We've...
We've collected
hermit crabs.
We've put them in the traps.
We rafted them out.
You know, if we can just
catch the one fish,
then we can use that as bait
and we'll catch more.
Right there.
Right there, right there.
STACEY:
Yep, there it is.
White, floatie, floatie...
Straight ahead.
RICHARD:
Damn well better be fish.
KELLY:
Oh, my gosh.
( humming fanfare )
Come on,
fishy, baby.
Fish are pretty stupid.
See what?
Bait hanging and
nothing moving.
Oh.
Empty.
These suck.
These do suck.
We're getting there,
getting to know
each other a little bit more.
I really want to learn
a little bit more about Stacey.
Because, you know--
I voted her off.
She thinks it was Rudy.
She even came up
to me and said
"Yeah, I think Rudy voted
me off, but that's okay
'cause he's next anyway."
STACEY:
I think after the vote
at the Island Council
Rudy realized that he was just
sort of a liability to us.
He was sitting around
barking orders
and not really helping out much.
We've all seen him eating
extra food and just doing
inappropriate things
in the kitchen.
Like, he's leaving the knives
out, they're getting rusty,
and he's opening
canned goods and fruit
without asking anybody.
I mean, we don't have
a lot of food here,
so I spoke up.
Actually,
Kelly, Sue and I decided
that somebody needed
to say something.
And we put all the canned goods
in one spot.
We're all going to vote
before we open something else.
RUDY:
Me and her wouldn't get along
if we were friends
on the outside...
I'd definitely avoid her.
She's too, uh,
prim-like, you know.
I mean, uh...
after about three weeks
out here in this jungle,
she's going to learn
a lesson, I think.
STACEY:
Boards underneath
or the support structure
underneath?
B.B.:
How are you working
on your back?
Tie that into there?
Yeah. Tie it into here.
You think
Well...cle worker?
JENNA:
We're getting things done
because B.B.
is such a great worker.
He gets us up.
We're moving stuff
this morning and everything.
He's doing that.
Whatever you say.
All right.
You've cut her
four times.
They're still
too short, right?
B.B.:
When you get done, you're
gonna have to take the broom
and sweep out this place.
COLLEEN:
I mean, really, B.B.
He's adorable.
I mean, who doesn't want to own
the B.B. action figure?
He's great. He's amazing.
He's got more stories
than anybody
I've ever met in my life.
I think he's a little bit out of
his element and he doesn't know
how to fix it without being
a little bit aggressive.
Ready? Careful.
Yeah. All right.
Hold tight.
The biggest workers are probably
Gretchen, Craig and... I can't
think of the lady's name
in the pink swimming suit,
but she,
she works her heart out.
You got
two hands, right?
I've got two, but
I-I'm keeping
myself up with one.
GRETCHEN:
Work ethic
is a big issue to B.B.
Regardless of their wonderful
personality or something,
you know, it comes down
to that with him.
RAMONA:
You're working your butt off
and he doesn't like to rest.
He's like this workaholic.
He just wants to get it done,
get it done, get it done,
and, yeah, that's great
sometimes,
but you can't push
yourself like that
and still, you know,
maintain...
I don't know. I just...
I don't see it lasting
too much longer.
What's our
fish situation?
Who doesn't have
chopsticks now?
GREG:
B.B., These are great.
Yeah, they work
really well.
Uh-huh.
B.B.
The only thing I ask you,
is take care of them
so I don't have
to redo this again,
'cause after
I make eight
I won't remember how
to make nine sets.
RAMONA:
At this point, no one wants
to have a confrontation
with him,
so, it's like,
whatever B.B. says, it's like
"Okay, B.B., yeah.
Whatever you want."
And, I don't know,
I guess, honestly,
if we were to ever lose
an immunity challenge
I think he'd probably be
the first one voted off.
RICHARD:
Rudy's cooking.
KELLY:
Oh, nice.
Whatcha cooking, Rude?
I'm going to make
the rice and a papaya.
Cool.
Beautiful..
Do we have
any lemon left?
Yeah, you can put it in
yourself.
RICHARD:
Sounds awesome.
Chef Rudy., Rude.
We're ready whenever.
We don't have any fish,
but we got the traps set.
RICHARD:
Rudy and I--
i-it's an interesting dynamic
because if he knew I were gay
that would probably be really
difficult for him, I think.
72 Years old, Navy vet.
I think it would just freak him.
But, he doesn't,
as far as I know, know that,
and I think he feels comfortable
talking to me.
I'm certainly comfortable
talking to him.
He's an interesting character.
DIRK:
Self-sufficient.lent review...
on male, I mean, I know,
you're not just homosexual.
I know gay guys don't like
to be called that
'cause you're not homosexual,
you're gay, you know.
No. I'm homosexual. Do we not
not like to be called that?
No, because it just...
No... it's only
classifying people
in sexual terms.
SUSAN:
It's a lifestyle.
Right.
Well, there is a lifestyle
associated with being gay,
but it's not something...
You can't say,
"I decided to be gay."
But it's been interesting
in this new environment
to kind of decide
when to say
what about yourselves.
I think there's
only one person
you got to worry about.
RICHARD:
Oh, I'm not worried
about him at all.
As people get to know me,
they learn who I am
and then eventually, over time,
find out I'm gay.
I've never once in my life
encountered prejudice
based on my being homosexual.
RUDY:
I was big-mouthing
the whole time coming over here
about being with homosexuals
and lesbians.
So I found out last night,
you know.
When he came up here
he said, uh, "You want to talk?"
I says,
"No, I don't want to talk."
And he was going to tell me
he was queer then.
The weather ain't
going to change.
If we went
six degrees below.
Where the hell
is Borneo?
That way?
RUDY:
The homosexual,
he's one of the nicest guys
I ever met
and he's good at what he does,
you know.
He's got leadership ability,
and if these people here
would listen to him,
he would take them a long way.
But anyway,
me and Richard got to be
pretty good friends--
not in a homosexual way,
that's for sure.
Make sure you get
this on TV.
Oh, boy, you better have a beer
in your hand
when you're doing this one,
Rudy.
RUDY:
He's a pretty good guy.
I don't know what my buddies
are going to say
when I get home, but...
I'll have to deal with that.
KELLY:
I'm thinking we should
dam off a part.
To walk over?
Yeah, well.
Now it's, like, satiated,
'cause I wanted papaya.
You don't
want it?
Well, then,
I'll eat it.
RAMONA:
I'm very, very finicky
and as hungry as I am,
if I really... if I eat that
I'm going to throw it up.
And I'd rather them eat it
and be able to swallow it
and digest it
than me to waste it, so...
I'll just drink water,
try to compensate.
Ramona's hurting big-time.
I feel bad for her,
'cause she wants so hard
to, you know, get into the mix
of things and help out
and do her job, do her part,
but she's just not feeling well.
JENNA:
You all right,
Ramona?
( coughing )
GRETCHEN:
I don't think
this is what she expected.
I don't think she'd ever quit.
I think she doesn't even want
to admit
that she's laying down a lot,
but, um, I think it's only
because she doesn't want to say
that she can't be successful
at something,
'cause I think she...
I think at home
she's very successful
at what she does.
B.B.:
Well...
I think the work-ethic problem
is-- doesn't ever change.
The people who are working work
and the people who rest
are resting and that's...
that's the way it is about 80,
85% of the time.
The laziest person is Ramona.
I mean, she just doesn't
contribute anything.
She probably hasn't worked
ten or 15 minutes in five days.
She's really a drag
because she drinks our water,
takes our... eats our food
and takes room in the hutch.
GERVASE:
He's such a hard worker.
If you're not working
as hard as him
you're not working hard.
I think it's just that simple.
I feel everybody's been pulling
their weight here.
Nobody's been slacking.
I mean, people have been sick.
People have been hurting
and I don't expect them to work.
GREG:
B.B.'s a good guy.
He's pretty strong-willed
and he's got his plan as well.
He's caring.
He demands respect.
Definitely feels the difference
between his age and other
people
and doesn't seem to want
to bridge that gap
as much as just be who he is.
We're probably about five
or six minutes away
from a delicious breakfast.
GRETCHEN:
You know, B.B.,
throw a lot more water in there.
You guys are like
backseat cooks.
RAMONA:
You're a backseat
everything,
so don't be
throwing stones.
I think they find me, probably,
abrasive, authoritarian.
There's probably a couple
of other adjectives
you could throw in there
that would probably work, too.
When you get to be 64 years old
I'll let you give
all the orders, okay?
I won't make
it that long.
B.B.
I don't care.
I'm not trying to win
a personality contest.
I just want to make my life here
as comfortable as possible
and then get the hell off.
It's really no problem.
It's just like
walking across
Oh, yeah. the river.
RAMONA:
Well, the whole
Colleen-and-Greg thing--
I don't know what's going on,
what's not going on,
but I kind of noticed
like a couple of times
they went off for fruit
or whatever.
GREG:
Colleen and I share
a similar way of looking
at everything that's happening.
Don't smile on swampie there.
COLLEEN:
Greg is great.
It's just good
to have a friend, you know.
Sometimes, when you come
to a country--
a foreign country--
a lot of times
you're really nervous
about all the mysteries
that are there.
You know,
you hear about malaria.
You hear about this,
you hear about that.
Those aren't worms;
those are leeches.
Nothing.
COLLEEN:
Like him,
walking around barefoot
and picking up things
and whatever,
you feel a lot more comfortable,
and the place becomes
more your home.
( Colleen chuckling )
Come on over
this way.
Oh, my God!
Oh, this is so fun.
GREG:
She's really fun to play with
because she's fun, energetic.
Oh, yeah.
She's, uh, rough and ready.
It's just, like, I'm actually
making a friend out here,
which I didn't think
was really possible.
RAMONA:
Greg and Colleen--
they had disappeared again.
And we were, like,
where are they?
I mean, they were gone
for, like, an hour.
You know, they come back
and we had no idea
where they'd gone,
what they'd done,
until that night,
you know, they were like
"Okay, we're going
to have game night."
And we played the All-new
Newly Stranded Survivor game.
( hooting and hollering )
GREG:
Today, we're going to play
the All-new Newly Stranded game.
( cheering )
RAMONA:
Basically, it was kind of like
a newlywed game.
Team one was Gretchen and B.B.
Team two was myself,
Jenna and Gervase,
and then, the third team
was Colleen and Joel.
If you were to describe your
favorite lovemaking position
as a food,
um, which food would that be
and why?
Oh...
Dude! Answer
the question!
I'm thinking, like,
Good & Plenty.
I don't know.
( shrieks )
Excellent.
RAMONA:
And so, of course,
Greg was the host
and he's just so wacky.
I love this guy.
Like, no matter what,
he will have you laughing
at least, like,
five times a day.
( laughing )
And completely unpalatable.
That is such a relief
to have somebody there
that's, like, the icebreaker.
GREG:
On to our next category, then.
Did you sleep last night
worrying about this thing?
I mean, I got
reason to worry.
GRETCHEN:
When we first got here,
we started arguing, B.B. and I,
about where to put the shelter
and I thought it should be
up in the canopy, you know,
out of the sun
and with some protection,
and he thought it should be
down on the beach.
B.B.:
Idle water won't hurt us.
GRETCHEN:
This morning we woke up
and we saw that the moon
was not yet full
and high tide came
almost to our doorstep.
B.B.:
This is going to
be a breakwater.
I want to get down there
far enough to where
the waves will come up over it
and start dumping sand.
One, two, three.
B.B.:
I already had my end up on two.
We started bringing logs down
and keep the waves
from breaking on the hut
'cause it's going
to wash away the support posts,
and so he admitted
that maybe I was right
about putting it back further,
he said
but he still doesn't
want it up in the canopy.
Said he never will sleep
up there, so...
All right,
hold it, Greg.
Right in there.
We're right in.
All the way over now.
Walk straight in
towards the hutch.
Damn it. Walk
straight in.
Okay, stop.
Put it down.
( screams )
Okay, steady.
No, no, no. Everybody,
let's don't rush this.
B.B.:
But I think that's
the way it ought to be.
Well, you can
disagree without being smart.
Well, how many times
do we have to say it?
I know; that's
not right.
Well, it may not be that right,
but how many times we got
to say-- make those decisions?
B.B., I thought we were
going to double up...
We did.
We doubled up
off three feet.
That's not going
to do it.
Yes, it will.
JOEL:
You know, if the sky was blue
and I said it was blue
he'd say it was red
just to disagree.
I can't let it
bring me down anymore.
If we're building a health gym,
a health facility,
I'll let you
do it.
So, if we're going
to have kids,
that's my job.
What does
that mean?
I mean, remarks
like that do
not help.
He makes
all of these great promises
and-and of what
he's going to do,
like catch fish
and do everything else.
He has not performed one thing
he said he'd do.
He reminds me of a guy that
when you buy him
for what he's worth
and sell him
for what he thinks he's worth,
you'd make $1 million.
I meant
significant water.
GREG:
Well, I think
they knock heads.
B.B.'s very strong-willed
and Joel is as well.
They don't back down
from one another
and that causes
a bit of friction--
a bit of chafing if you want
to put it in island terms.
We got a float.
I'm definitely catching
a fish today.
Sea bass or salmon
or whatever the hell
we can get out of this ocean.
Fish is a priority right now.
Fish is very much a priority.
Now that we have the fire, we
need something to cook it in.
Hey, where's super pole?
This is so super pole.
Look at this--
I got the man's grip.
Where's your hook?
We're working--
it's right underneath.
This sinker's a free-floating
float and all I do
is I take the line out,
line out,
cast home
that super pole.
Then I reel in
the big one.
Not too shabby.
SUSAN:
Sean sits there for five hours
and builds a super pole
and doesn't catch anything
with it.
SEAN:
Been fishing all day today
and still nothing.
I don't even get a nibble.
So that's, you know,
really dissatisfying.
Get anything, Stacey?
No.
SUSAN:
I told him
it was a waste of time.
"Oh, no, it's not
a waste of time."
"Did you catch any fish?"
"No."
RICHARD:
He's, um, really
wanting to get fish.
Hadn't been able to bring any
in, and I think that was
really starting
to eat at him.
Maybe the area's overfished
or something.
We'll figure it out
sooner or later.
( chuckling )
( indistinct talking )
You washing your clothes
in our food container?
He's washing
his clothes
in freshwater.
He's washing his clothes
with the canteen water?
Yeah.
It's unbelievable, man.
JOEL:
When we get back, we're going
to make some rice, we're happy.
First thing he does
is he washes his T-shirt
in the kettle we're going
to cook the rice in.
Every canteen was empty
and the sun's going down.
It's starting to rain.
When are we going
to get water, you know?
You think I have time
to go now?
No.
I wasn't sure I'd have time,
so it's stupid to go up there.
There's places
where you can, you know,
it's wet now
'cause it was raining
and you can barely walk.
She's a little upset, too,
that...
The freshwater for some
cleansing supplies.
Yeah.
I thought we would
discuss this
from the beginning.
Before anybody
does anything,
we got to vote
on whatever
we're doing.
Now that's a
canteen of water.
But you can't
just do that.
We can't go back
to the water hole tonight
because we'll get lost.
I don't mind. I'll go.
No, we can't.
It's getting dark
and it's raining.
...then Why?re hurt.
If you get hurt,
then we all lose.
But that's not
the point.
B.B.:
I'm not going to get hurt
if I go after water.
B.B., please. B.B.
It is not about "I."
It's about us.
You're missing
the whole point.ng.
You're the one
who brought it up.
I didn't say a word.
You know, if that
was your canteen
that's cool.
There you go.
I don't even know
if that's cool,
because if you get dehydrated
and we have to compete,
we all lose.
I'm not imposing my...
You can't do anything here
without everybody agreeing.
We all have to agree
what we're going to do.
That's the whole thing.
I've been working my ass off
and the lot of you have been
laying on your ass watching me,
so don't give me
any of that ...
Everyone's been
working their
ass off.
Bull ...
Hey, we've
all been working.
I've worked 20 times
as much as you.
I'm not faulting you,
but when you start getting
on my ass about working...
That's what you think.
You didn't take one trek
in this jungle yet.
Your ass has been
sitting down here
chillin'.
GERVASE:
If B.B. thinks anybody
on our tribe is slacking,
the heat is affecting him.
Everybody on our tribe
is working hard.
I mean, everybody
has different jobs.
Building the shelter
is probably the hardest job.
He took that challenge on
so somebody going out there
trying to catch some fish
might not look that important,
but it's just as important.
I didn't want this
to turn into this.
It's going to turn
into this.
You knew it was.
I mean, there's no
other way around it.
This is the meeting
we were talking about
we needed to have.
You can't be making decisions
on your own.
I'll try to at least get
all eight of us here for this,
and then we'll talk.
I'm going after water.
B.B.:
I'm not voting
when I wash my clothes.
No one's going to tell me
when I can do stuff like that.
First place,
this is not a democracy.
I'll vote on things
that don't matter,
but things that matter, uh,
and my survival...
and... my comfort,
I'm not going to vote.
Throughout their time
on the island
the tribes will compete
in a series of challenges.
They'll receive messages
notifying them
of these competitions
at their tree mail.
Lose, face Tribal Council
where you must vote
one member off the island.
You did?
We got something.
( chuckles )
Info, info.
"You've been cordially invited
to the first annual
"Starving Survivor's Buffet.
"The meal will feature
local delicacies
"and will be served al fresco
in the shadow of the banyan tree
along the Lari-Lari trail."
Oh, gosh, this is about
eating disgusting things!
Oh! Can you imagine?!
I bet you're right.
Eating disgusting things.
( groans )
I don't know.
I'm going to pull out
some of the maps.
Eating bugs.
We're going
to be eating some bugs tonight.
Come on, man. I love bugs.
I know you do.
Huh?
RUDY:
"And will be served al fresco
in the shadow of the banyan tree
along the Lari-Lari trail."
Hmm, sounds tasty.
Oh, I'll swallow everything.
You won't even eat rice.
What are you talking about?
This is for immunity.
That's different.
Let's have a little
strategy meeting
for the immunity
challenge.
Okay.
I think we ought
to consider how
we're going to do it.
Whether we even
want to win it.
'Cause I think...
Yes, we want
to win it.
No, I want
to talk about it
'cause I think
we ought to think
about lightening
the load here.
I'm not going to quit,
but if I can engineer
an escape route for myself
and do it right, do it ethically
and do it correctly,
then, sure, I'll do it.
I don't agree with that...
with quitting or engineering
something just to save face.
I think he's trying
to save face
before getting voted off
because I don't think
he would have come here
if that was the case.
What's the point of coming
all this way,
going through all the crap
we had to go through
to get here,
for you to all of a sudden
decide
that you want to get voted off.
B.B., you can put
up with this
for a little longer.
The name of the game
is to reduce the tribe.
is to stay together
as long as you can.
Yeah, to survive.
To survive.
Sometimes strategy-wise,
it might be best.
You have a chance
to go, everyone.
Oh, I understand that,
but I'm just saying
I think we ought to
at least decide
what we want to do.
We want to win.
Win.
Then the subject's closed.
JEFF:
This is the immunity idol.
The tribe holding the idol
does not have to hike
to Tribal Council
and vote one of their own
off the island.
The Pagong Tribe won
last week's immunity challenge
"Quest for Fire."
We're just not going
to let this out!
JEFF:
Win today's challenge,
win the idol
and immunity from tonight's
Tribal Council.
Yeah, baby!
( all cheering )
JEFF:
Welcome.
Right on!
Thank you.
Grab a seat, guys.
How's it going?
Pagong, thanks
for bringing back
the immunity idol.
It's up for grabs again.
Losing tribe,
you know the drill.
You go to Tribal Council,
one of your members
gets voted off,
not a fun place to go.
I know you guys probably
been six days without food.
So, I went out,
I looked long and hard
to find a true local delicacy.
And we turned it
into an immunity competition,
so let me just give you
a visual.
Oh, God.
Gross!
Yeah. In Borneo,
this is considered
like sushi.
( cheering and groaning )
Everybody, just take one.
Now, these will swim away.
Gerv's going to
have to eat it!
JEFF:
Put it on
your plate
and don't let
it crawl away.
They're called,
uh, "puton."
These are just
beetle larvae.
That's all they are.
I didn't want to know that.
I was better not knowing.
Aw! Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah!
B.B.:
Aw, look at
that thing go.
( loud groan )
JEFF:
Okay, the rules of the game
are simple:
The first person
who refuses to eat a bug
loses immunity for their tribe.
Lose immunity, your tribe
must vote one of its members
off the island
at tonight's Tribal Council.
Guys, bon appetit.
Not the head?
Bite the head off.
Just hold it by the head
and take and bite it.
But get all
of it, Gervase.
Don't just get the tail.
SUSAN:
Yeah, I wouldn't
eat the head, man.
RICHARD:
Yeah, Dirk.
SUSAN:
Yeah, Dirk!
Come on!
COLLEEN:
Come on, Gervase!
JENNA:
Eat it!
COLLEEN:
Go, Dirk.
JENNA:
We're doing it
for the what, Gervase?
( all yelling )
Keep going.
RAMONA:
Put it in your mouth!
Put it
in your mouth!
( Gervase yells )
GRETCHEN:
Quick! Come on, quick!
JENNA:
Gervase!
COLLEEN:
Gervase,
you've got it.
Come on, man.
I can't do it!
GREG:
Stay focused, guys.
Don't think
about it.
JENNA:
Close your eyes.
Can we bite the
head off first?
( groaning )
I can't do it!
If you've been
to Chinese restaurants,
you've eaten worse;
they're just smaller.
( groans )
Grab it by the head
and stick it in your mouth.
One!
Two!
I can't do it!
Ew!vase!
Yuck, yuck, yuck,
yuck, yuck, yuck!
JEFF:
Gervase, I'm going
to count to five--
countdown
from five.
Oh, Gervase,
if you lose...
Starting now.
Prepare yourself.
Here comes the count.
Five...
four...
three...
two...
I'm going to do it!
One...
Yes! Yeah!
Yes!
Yeah! Yeah!
( cheering and groaning )
RAMONA:
He swallowed it!
JEFF:
Even up. We're moving
down next door.
Gretchen and Sean.
Jeff.
JEFF:
You're good.
Nice work.
Ow! Yeah!
( cheering )
Yeah, baby.
Eat it whole,
you guys.
There you go,
come on.
SEAN:
There you go,
big man.
Ah, gone.
Wow.
I'm chewing.
JEFF:
Water's right there
in the pitcher.
Hey, Richard.
Come on, baby.
Can we take
the head off now?
JEFF:
I'm going to come down
there and check, though.
I don't want to...
All right.
All right, Greg.
GRETCHEN:
It's like chicken.
JEFF:
Yeah, hold them
up for me, okay.
Let me see that.
( laughter )
Oh...
GERVASE:
Good one,
Colleen.
JEFF:
Hit it, Sue.
GERVASE:
Yeah, baby!
JEFF:
B.B., let me see you, here.
( cheering )
( whooping )
Great. Well,
I kind of anticipated
you might enjoy this,
so we have a tie-breaker round.
Pagong, you can pick
who you perceive to be
their most squeamish member,
the member least likely
to want to eat.
Tagi, you pick their
most squeamish member,
the person you think...
I think Gervase.
STACEY:
You know what,
maybe they're
faking us out.
Pick him.
JOEL:
Gervase will go.
He's a team player.
Pagong, who're you guys
going with?
RAMONA:
I think Stacey.
STACEY:
Okay.
So, is that your choice?
Stacey and Gervase?
Okay, Stacey, come down here
and switch places with Dirk.
COLLEEN:
Come on, Gervase!
RICHARD:
Go, Stacey, baby.
It's up to you, baby.
All right.
You guys ready?
Yeah.
You ready?
I want to make
the rules very clear--
each reach in
and grab two of these.
You'll wash them in that bowl;
you'll put them in your bowl.
When I tell you to go, you go.
First one done with both
wins immunity for their team.
Here we go-- grab two each
and wash them off.
You got it.
Here you go, guys.
I liked it before.
Shall we eat
at the same time?
Ahh!
KELLY:
Stace!n, baby.
We'll all do it
at the same time.
COLLEEN:
Immunity, Gervase.
It's all about
immunity.
B.B.:
Come on!
JEFF:
We're not going yet.
I'm going to say,
"Three, two, one, eat."
You grab on "eat."
Get your hands down
at your waist.
DIRK:
Here we go, Stace.
JOEL:
Close your eyes
and kill them, man.
JEFF:
Here we go, guys:
Three, two, one. Eat!
Go, Gervase, go!
Go, Gervase!
SEAN:
Swallow!
Open!
( cheering )
JEFF:
Tagi!
Yes!
Whoo!, guys.
DIRK:
All right!
Good..
DIRK:
Stacey!
Good job, man.
Man, I just got
some protein!
RICHARD:
Nice bug-eating.
( whooping )
SEAN:
Stacey thinks she can
do anything just like I do,
and she really did her own.
I think what really
pulled her through
was eating those two bugs
in lightning speed,
because I think
she impressed a lot people,
pulled her own weight.
I think that's when she finally
got accepted amongst the girls.
JEFF:
Unfortunately, you guys
are coming
to Tribal Council tonight.
And I'll just want to give you
a little advance warning:
It is a long walk.
It's a walk through the jungle,
in the dark.
Bring some sticks.
Tagi ran into a lot of snakes.
Here's a map, follow it.
Uh, tonight, you will have
to vote one member
of your team off.
You can head back.
( bird whistling )
RAMONA:
Tribal council--
it's kind of like...
judgment day on Earth, kind of,
and that's-that's
like so daunting.
You're like, "Whoa."
I mean, you have to stand
in judgment of your maker,
and in this case, of, like,
your fellow tribe members.
My length of stay
on the island depends
on either what, like,
somebody thinks of me
or what they don't think of me
or of my abilities.
I'm not exactly a control freak,
but I kind of like to be
in control of things,
and I have no control
over whether I stay or go.
My vote would be
I would vote Ramona off
because B.B. is
such a great wor... gets us up.
He... We're moving stuff
this morning and everything.
I mean,
we're getting things done
because B.B.'s there, too.
He's doing that.
As soon as we had breakfast,
Ramona was back in bed.
I think it's, uh, likely
B.B. will be
the first one voted off.
I think he pretty much...
he dug his own grave.
Now he's saying he wants to go.
So, if that's what he wants,
that's fine.
B.B.:
The first two people
that I would consider voting
out of here, besides myself,
would be, uh...
Joel and, uh... Ramona.
If I get voted off,
I'll give you this
and you wear it
as a tube top.
All right, good, yeah...
and I'm leaving my beach towel.
GRETCHEN:
Even though we've only known
each other
for such a short time
I think we-we've bonded already.
I think that's how everybody
was feeling.
Some people, you know,
showed it
and some people didn't.
I'm going to take my
chopsticks with me.
Maybe somebody needs chopsticks.
I can sell them on the side
and make a little
extra money.
( chuckles )
You know?
( mumbles )
Huh?
B.B.:
They got to think long and hard
before they vote me out
because I think
I contribute a lot.
If Gretchen or I
would leave this tribe,
that'd be like
dropping an atomic bomb here.
( waves crashing )
JEFF:
This is Tribal Council,
where each week, one member
will be voted off the island.
Pagong must now make
the dreaded hike
to the Tribal Council.
Despite their
initial successes,
the tribe is in turmoil.
B.B.'s butting heads
with the rest of the tribe,
Ramona has been ill,
and their shelter
is in danger
of being washed away.
Soon we'll find out
if losing a member
is what is needed
to bring this tribe together.
( birds chirping )
( gong sounds )
( birds singing )
We begin Tribal Council
with the ritual.
Behind each of you is a torch.
I'd like you to grab the torch
and approach the fire.
Go ahead and dip
your torches in,
and once they're lighted,
put them back in their slots
and have a seat.
We do this because--
as I'm sure you've figured out--
on the island,
fire represents life.
These torches now represent
your life, your identity
here at Tribal Council,
and you will bring them back
with you to each council.
Go ahead and have a seat.
Well, having made the, uh, trek
from your guys' camp to here,
I know what a long one it is--
monitor lizards, snakes--
but it's not by accident
the Tribal Council is located
in the center of the jungle.
What happens here is sacred,
needs to be respected.
The way you've handled yourself
will either come back
to help you,
or it may come back
to haunt you,
but those actions
will play a part
as we'll find out tonight.
If you look over here,
you'll see the only
unlit staff on this ruin.
That represents Sonja--
the first person
voted off the island.
Tonight, one of you
will have your flame
extinguished,
and you will go home.
It's tough, but that's
the nature of Tribal Council,
the way it's set up.
So, before we get to the vote,
Colleen, what was your take
on what went down in terms
of who stepped forward
to take the reins?
I mean,
I think we have
two or three strong leaders
in our group, definitely,
and they took, uh...
they guided the rest of us
into, uh, doing the right things
and getting everything done.
I mean, we have
a great place now,
thanks to them, I think.
Gervase, what are you
feeling right now
first time at Tribal Council,
knowing what you're going
to have to do tonight?
I-I just feel bad.
You know, I kind of feel
like I let my team down
by, uh... not winning,
but, uh...
I mean, that's-that's
really about it, you know.
I-I just wish
we kicked their butt.
Didn't happen that way,
you know, but...
JEFF:
Jenna, you've been
a little bit
of a cheerleader
for the group.
So, how does this play for you,
coming over here,
having to vote one person off?
It's unfair.
We've really bonded,
so to kick one of us off
is like losing a family member,
and then it's going to be
a large, empty gap
in the bed tonight.
All right.
Let me explain
how the voting works.
One by one, starting with B.B.,
you come along here,
go across
this bridge
into our voting
confessional.
There's a piece of paper.
You need to write the name
of the person
you're voting off
in large, clear
block letters.
Hold it up.
Speak your piece.
All right.
It's time to vote.
B.B., you're up.
B.B.:
Uh, I think that
this, uh, person contributed
probably the least of anyone
in all of our efforts.
I chose B.B. 'cause he was like
a get-out-of-jail-free card.
He said that he was ready to go,
and he'd done
what he came to do,
and he might not have been
my first choice
if he wasn't ready to go home,
because he certainly
is a hard worker
and he kicked some butt.
I think it's time
for Ramona to go.
She's a strong challenger,
but it seems like she, uh...
she doesn't want to be
a part of the...
or is struggling with being
part of the group life
that we have there.
Uh, I voted him off
because he's about
the only choice
we had right now.
Uh, we all talked
about other ones, but, uh...
right now,
he's just the best choice
because we have to win
the next competitions.
Unfortunately, we had to do it.
Sorry, man.
JEFF:
Well, obviously, there are a lot
of reasons
why you guys are here.
$1 million, enough reason
probably for anybody,
and I'm sure
there are some of you
who may have different reasons
or additional reasons.
Regardless, to achieve your goal
you have to survive
tonight's Tribal Council.
One of you won't.
I'll go tally the votes.
Before I read the votes,
I just want to say that
once the decision has been made,
it is final.
I'll guide you through this,
but you'll be asked
to leave the island immediately.
No good-byes.
All right,
let's count the votes.
First vote: "B.B."
"Ramona."
"B.B."
That's two votes for Ramona,
two votes for B.B.
"B.B."
The last vote
is irrelevant.
B.B., I need to have
you grab your torch
and bring it to me.
Go ahead and
slide over here.
B.B., the tribe
has spoken.
It's time
for you to go.
All right.
Good-bye.
JEFF:
To the rest of you,
uh, congratulations.
You survived
your first Tribal Council.
Not a fun process,
but one you'll have to do again.
You can take your torches
and head back to camp.
Next week on Survivor:
My testimony is not something
I'm afraid to share.
When Christ came,
he opened the door
to every human being.
I can only take
so much preaching.
Dirk's about driving me wild
with that.
The "oomph" is a little gone.
I think that not eating
is a factor of our mood.
I'm so ready to eat rat.
I want to gut him, bone him
and...
Surf and turf.
Minnows and rats.
I'm a little sad
to leave these people
because after the last six days,
you know, we've gotten
pretty close, all of us.
There isn't anybody
in that group I don't like.
Some I like more than others,
but that's normal.
And I hope that I showed them
a little bit of work ethic;
that I don't back off
from-from what I did.
I think what I did
was the right way.