>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Two tribes were abandoned in the
middle of the Australian
outback...
>> AMBER: Ogakor.
>> MARALYN: Ogakor.
>> MICHAEL: Kucha.
>> DEBB: We're Kucha?
>> JEFF: ...and had to make a
treacherous hike to find their
camps.
>> AMBER: I'm a little tired.
This rice is very heavy.
>> JEFF: But not everybody could
stomach the trek.
>> JEFF V.: All of a sudden I
just got sort of nauseous, and I
kept thinking to myself, "I'm
not going to get sick."
( retching )
>> JEFF: At Ogakor, tensions
simmered between Keith and
Jerri.
>> JERRI: I don't even really
want to attempt to start a fire
until we get it where we want to
keep it.
>> KEITH: I think we start the
fire-- we take it where we want
to.
>> JERRI: He might very well not
even be aware of some of the
condescending remarks he made to
me, but I'm not the kind of
person to just let it slide off
my back.
>> JEFF: At Kucha, there wasn't
enough food to put in their
mouths...
>> JEFF V.: I'm looking at bugs.
>> JEFF: ...but there was plenty
of Kimmi's mouth to go around.
>> KIMMI: We was back-to-back,
he farted in my... it
rebounded...
>> JEFF V.: Kimmi will not shut
up.
I just want to grab her by the
neck and shake the ... out of
her.
>> JEFF: Ogakor won the immunity
challenge...
The immunity idol.
...so Kucha had to make the long
hike to Tribal Council.
Debb was the first person voted
out.
The tribe has spoken.
15 People left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> JEFF V.: I saw Mike getting
up really early.
The sun was just coming up.
Everybody was asleep, and I woke
up, and I saw Mike messing
around the fire and putting
stuff on the pot, and I couldn't
understand what he was doing.
And so as we were waking up, we
realized he put rice on, and
nobody said anything about
eating rice.
Nobody said they were hungry.
And he left.
He just put the rice on, and he
left.
>> ALICIA: Are you making rice?
>> JEFF V.: Mike is.
>> ALICIA: Mike's making rice
already?
>> JEFF V.: I hope everybody's
hungry.
I'm not hungry at all.
That was totally not cool.
>> ALICIA: No, I don't think
that was good.
When it comes to food, it has to
be a group decision, since we
don't have much.
Mike was hungry.
That's why he did that.
And that is another indication
of Mike being Mike, about
himself.
>> MICHAEL: Everyday we've been
having breakfast first thing in
the morning, and I got up, and I
thought I was being really
helpful, and I cleaned the pot,
and I boiled the water, and I
made the rice, and I was going
to have a warm meal for
everybody when they woke up.
Dig in, let's go.
>> ALICIA: It's like rice
porridge.
>> JEFF V.: It cooked too long,
and it was mashy and just nasty.
>> KIMMI: You know what?
We could use this as the
wallpaper glue to hold
everything together.
>> MICHAEL: It was odd that in
fact it not only wasn't
appreciated, they didn't like
it.
>> KIMMI: Mike, baby, we love
you, but you're not qualified.
>> MICHAEL: I think people are
starting to get a little bit
edgy without food, and they
don't realize how bad it's going
to get.
I'm a student of nutrition, and
I know what this is doing to my
body.
But these other people have no
idea.
If they did, they would be out
fishing and hunting for food.
But they don't.
I guess maybe the way that I can
convince them of the importance
of the food is by catching a lot
of it and then feeling full one
time and seeing what happens to
their body and how much energy
they have.
Maybe that's how I can convince
them.
>> KEL: Maralyn, I'm going to go
out and check the trap.
>> MARALYN: Okay.
>> MITCHELL: Kel is like the
fisherman of the group.
He's very persistent in that
area, and part of me thinks it's
because he feels if he does
catch a fish, that might, um,
keep him here longer.
>> MARALYN: Good luck.
>> KEL: Thank you.
Thank you.
>> MARALYN: There's a time to be
energized, and there's a time to
just chill out.
So we're going to the family
whirlpool.
( laughter )
>> MARALYN: This will feel so
good.
You'll be in ecstasy.
( indistinct chatter )
>> JERRI: Look at us, just
hanging out like we're on
vacation.
This is great.
>> KEL: Our food strategy right
now is rice.
I mean, rice is our staple.
I don't see that rice lasting us
more than ten days.
We do need to get some fish out
of this river.
>> KEITH: Our plan for getting
food is, uh...
We don't really have a good
plan, actually.
No fish.
Are we worried if there's no
fish in the water?
>> COLBY: I'm not worried.
>> MITCHELL: There ain't no fish
in this water, I'll tell you
that.
I say stop wasting the energy
on fishing.
And I don't think there's any
fish out there.
( laughs )
>> KEL: We've got some great
hooks that were in the crate.
but I don't have any fishing
line.
And so what I've had to use is
twine, and twine, um, is not as
great as fishing line-- it
breaks, you have to weave it
together to get through the
hole.
The fish can see it, obviously,
and plus the twine floats, so I
have to tie a rock to the twine
to make the twine sink which
makes it even more noticeable to
the fish.
>> COLBY: Kel's done a little
bit of fishing which just, I
mean, come on, the guy couldn't
fish a rubber ducky out of the
bathtub.
The bait choices, the-the
lines...
He's just going about it the
wrong way.
>> KEL: So I've been trying to
fish every day, and I've been
unsuccessful, but I'm not going
to quit.
I'm going to keep on doing it
and doing it and doing it until
I can find a great fishing spot
or a technique that works.
>> JERRI: Believe me, when he
goes out, I'm hoping more than
anybody that he's going to come
back with some fish and some
shrimp, and he'll have a big
seafood buffet.
Any luck out there?
>> KEL: No, but there are fish
out there.
I saw quite a few.
>> JERRI But it's not happening.
And it's... ( laughs )
He's just, he's not a
fisherman, obviously.
He should keep his day job.
( laughing )
>> JEFF V.: Oh, wow.
>> ALICIA: Whoa.
This is big time.
>> JEFF V.: It's a reward.
>> ALICIA: There we go.
>> JEFF V.: "A leap of faith is
not for the skilled.
Just step off the edge, try not
to get killed.
Like Sundance and Butch..."
>> ALICIA ( gasps ): We're
jumping off a cliff.
>> JEFF V.: "...you'll jump from
a cliff.
Count on your friends while
you're set adrift."
>> ALICIA: You guys?
>> JEFF V.: We've got a big one.
>> ALICIA: Did anybody
see Sundance?
We get two blankets if we
win.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh.
>> ALICIA: Feel it.
Two full-size blankets.
>> NICK: How nice it'll be
with blankets, man.
>> ALICIA: Oh, my God.
We'll definitely sleep through
the night if we have blankets.
>> KIMMI: Everybody has to jump?
>> NICK: You're jumping off a
cliff, bad boy.
>> JEFF V.: Can you jump off a
cliff?
>> RODGER: Into what?
>> JEFF V.: Into water.
>> RODGER: "Step off the edge"?
That's-that's... that's going
over something.
And we're off the edge.
>> NICK: Yeah, I'm psyched.
>> RODGER: "And try not to get
killed."
Today's challenge is, I
believe, is probably going to be
jumping off a cliff into some
water.
Water is not mine finest... my
uh, finest point, so, uh, I'm a
little apprehension.
But, uh, I figure if the rest of
them can do it, I can, too,
so I'm going to give it a shot.
>> JEFF V.: We got his back.
We got your back.
Rodger is the only one that I'm
a little iffy about.
I think everybody else is going
to go over it.
But he can't swim.
He can tread water, lightly.
>> RODGER: I just, basically,
learned to swim right before we
came out here.
Plus I'm... I really got a
little fear of heights, too.
I mean, you're talking to a guy
that wouldn't even ride the
Ferris wheel at the fairs,
'cause I just-just never did
like heights.
>> JEFF: What's up, guys?
This is a reward challenge.
It's called "Butch Cassidy" and
you're playing for two warm
blankets.
It is the rainy season.
They're probably going to come
in handy.
The game is this:
There are two crates, one for
each tribe, anchored out in the
water below.
Your challenge:
Get your tribe's crate across
the finish line at the old
miner's camp first.
Winners keep the blankets that
are sealed inside.
One member from each tribe, on
my start, is going to jump off
this cliff, they'll swim out and
grab on to the crate.
And then the next member will
jump off and swim out.
You can't jump until the person
in front of you has touched the
crate.
Once all the members from the
tribe have arrived, you've got
to dive down, unhook the crate
from its anchor, and then swim
with it down the river through
the rapids and make your way up
the beach.
First tribe to get their crate
onto the platform at the end
wins the challenge and the
blankets.
>> ALICIA: Let's go, Kucha.
( indistinct conversations )
Just run and jump and work
magic.
>> JEFF: Survivors ready?
Go!
( excited shouting, whooping )
>> JEFF V.: Go, Mike!
>> MITCHELL: Go, go, go, go!
( indistinct shouting )
>> JEFF V.: Go left, Mike.
Go left.
( excited shouting )
>> ALICIA: Go! Go!
>> ALICIA: Go right, go right!
>> NICK: Go right!
>> COLBY: That a way, Mitchell.
Go, Mitch, go!
>> MARALYN: Come on, Mitchell!
>> Go!
( laughter )
>> Oh, my God.
>> Go...!
( excited shouting )
( yelling )
>> Good job! Go! Go! Go!
>> Come on! Go! Go! Go! Go!
( excited shouting )
>> Come on, Rodger!
Let's go...
( indistinct shouting )
You can do it!
>> Come on, Rodger.
( indistinct shouting )
>> Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go
( excited shouting )
>> Come on, Rodger!
>> Come on, Rodger.
You can do it.
>> Come on, Rodger, you can do
it!
>> Come on, Rodger!
>> KIMMI: You can do it, Rodger!
>> ELISABETH: Let's go.
Here we go.
>> JERRI: Go!
( indistinct shouting )
>> KEL: Go!
>> ALICIA: Come on, grab on.
( indistinct shouting )
>> ALICIA: Ready? Go.
Come on, come on.
>> JEFF V.: Did you get it?
>> NICK: I got it.
>> JEFF V.: Go! Go!
>> ALICIA: Go! Go!
>> Good job. Pull!
( instinct shouting )
>> ALICIA: Nobody gives up.
Nobody gives up.
>> ELISABETH: Go, Kucha.
>> MARALYN: Oh, my God.
>> ELISABETH: Hang right!
Hang right!
( indistinct shouting )
( panting )
>> JEFF V.: Under the bottom...
>> ALICIA: Guys, get those...
>> AMBER: Oh, the sand's so hot!
( indistinct talking )
>> MICHAEL: One, two, three.
( whooping )
( panting, sighing )
>> AMBER: Good job, guys.
>> RODGER: I'm glad that's over.
>> ELISABETH: You've swam more
than you've ever swum in your
life.
>> JEFF: Guys, open that crate
up-- blankets inside.
You guys are on a hot streak.
Two in a row.
>> JERRI: I want to sleep one
good night.
>> COLBY: Did you sleep good
last night?
>> JERRI: No.
>> COLBY: Neither did I.
>> MARALYN: You know, all it
takes is one small mound in the
ground to really screw with your
body bad.
( scattered chuckling )
>> TINA: You know, we're not
getting eight hours' sleep.
We're not getting, you know, but
a handful of food a day.
But, you know, this is the game
we signed up to play.
>> KEITH: You guys hungry?
>> MARALYN: Yes.
>> JERRI: Are you cooking?
>> AMBER: Keith said he's a
chef, but, and it's not that I
don't believe it-- he can't
cook very well, you know?
And I'm not doubting his talent.
But I think it might be that
he's adding, maybe, too much
water to the rice.
>> TINA: It's pasty.
It tastes like glue.
It just... in your mouth it goes
( smacking )
It's just horrible, and I can't
eat it.
>> It just... it didn't make
sense.
It didn't make sense.
Like, how could a gourmet chef
not know how to make rice?
There's a bunch more things we
can have than rice, and I'm
ready to start making some of
them.
I remembered that with flour and
water you can create some sort
of dough.
>> KEITH: You know what we can
do, while you're doing that?
We're going to go get some more
wood.
>> JERRI: All right.
>> KEITH: So we'll be back in a
little while.
>> JERRI: Keith is very
threatened by the fact that I
made this tortilla this morning.
That's why... I heard them when
they went up on the hill, and
they were gathering wood, he was
talking, again, about what he's
going to do with the rice and
the vegetables and this...
You know, you just have to
laugh.
You just have to laugh.
( giggling )
>> KEITH: So there's so much
work to do as a team that, uh,
and it's hard, physical labor to
come up here and grab all these
big logs and stuff and throw
them down.
So, if she wants to cook some
tortillas for breakfast, I think
it's fantastic.
Actually, it's a break for me,
you know?
No... ( chuckles ) no worries,
mate.
>> JERRI: I felt a little bit
bad about it, but at the same
time, you know, I felt like it
was time for somebody to come in
and take charge and change the
food situation.
Go ahead.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
It is so good.
>> TINA: Thank you.
>> JERRI: Ah, you're welcome.
>> AMBER: I love it!
I love it.
>> JERRI: We will eat today.
>> AMBER: Slap me five.
>> TINA: Jerri's going to take
that job over, which I hope
doesn't hurt Keith's feelings.
You know, I mean, that's his
area, and it's kind of a slap in
the face.
>> KEL: Thanks, Jerri.
>> JERRI: Today's communion.
>> MITCHELL: Wow.
>> KEITH: Finest the restaurant
in the world couldn't have made
those that nice.
>> JERRI: Keith has gone out of
his way to compliment me a lot
now, to, like, try and smooth
the edges.
And I see... I mean, I see right
through it.
I don't-I don't think his
compliments are necessarily very
genuine.
>> KEITH: That is good.
I'm so glad they put wheat in
there.
>> COLBY: Thanks, Jerri.
>> JERRI: You know, the morale
right now is kind of low, but I
think the tortilla made
everybody spark up, so I'm
really stoked about that.
And I got a few other tricks to
pull out of my sleeve.
>> MICHAEL: I want to bring food
today.
If I can keep providing food, I
absolutely am sure I will make
the merger.
If I can't, I become vulnerable.
I've been thinking a lot about
the fact that at Tribal Council
it came out that I was the
leader, and I don't really want
to be seen as the leader.
So if I can get something, I'll
lay real low on the other
leadership areas and just be the
food guy.
>> KIMMI: We got fish!
It looks like you just went to
the fish market with all that
fish.
>> ALICIA: Look at that.
Who's better than you right
now?
There's nobody I can think of.
>> JEFF V.: When other people
catch a fish, they just catch a
fish.
But when Mike catches it, there
are trumpets that blare and
angels that sing.
And, you know, everybody's got
to sit down and gather round him
and hold his hands and watch him
carve it out.
>> MICHAEL: Ow.
Here you go.
>> ALICIA: Wow!
>> MICHAEL: Dear God, you know I
said a lot of prayers today, and
You answered them with fish for
us.
And I am so happy to be able to
provide fish for the troops.
I know that this could easily
get turned around in some way to
make me be the leader of the
tribe, but this meal is, from
the bottom of my heart, makes me
so happy to be able to provide
for everybody here.
So... thanks for that.
>> NICK: Amen.
>> ALICIA: Amen.
>> RODGER: Good job.
>> KIMMI: Mike thanked God for
making him the leader of the
tribe.
I don't know when he was
anointed, but apparently, my
back was turned at that moment.
>> MICHAEL: Oh, my God.
>> RODGER: Well, get you another
bite.
>> MICHAEL: No, no, no.
Take one bite and just keep
passing them...
>> RODGER: Michael does like to
be in the limelight.
I don't think there's any doubt
about that.
But as long as Mike keeps
delivering the food though,
that's going to be a hard one to
knock off, you know.
>> ALICIA: He really thinks he
is leader of this tribe.
I'm telling you now that there
are people in this tribe that
want to vote him off already.
>> MARALYN: I am very
disappointed at what happened
five minutes ago.
Jerri reported to the rest of us
that she had seen Kel chewing a
brown substance.
What she thought was beef jerky.
>> JERRI: And I saw him put
something in his mouth and it
was like dark brown colored,
shredded looking sort of thing.
>> MITCHELL: Jerri blatantly
that said she saw something that
looked just like beef jerky go
into his mouth.
And I... I believe her,
actually.
>> JERRI: I guarantee it was.
>> AMBER: I saw him chewing, but
you saw...
>> COLBY: I saw him chewing,
too.
>> JERRI: I mean to have your
own team member possibly be
holding food behind you and
surviving on their own little
private stash while the rest of
us are... starving basically is
not a good way to start off on
the right foot with a bunch of
strangers.
Because to think that someone in
our own tribe would be, you
know, sneaking in extra stuff,
especially food.
>> MITCHELL: Well, if you're
eating anything that we weren't
eating, then that's unfair to
the rest of us.
>> TINA: If he had beef jerky,
I'd kill him dead.
>> MARALYN: The pot starts to
boil.
While Kel was up on the hill,
they rifled through his bag.
>> TINA: You know, it was like a
big feeding frenzy.
You know, "Kel's got beef
jerky."
And they said, "Look in his
backpack real quick."
And I was standing right there,
and I did it.
And there wasn't anything in
there at all.
But still and yet, all I was
thinking about, "If I find beef
jerky in here, it's going to be
ugly."
>> COLBY: He's snacking up
there, I know it.
( scattered chuckling )
>> MARALYN: Ouch.
Within earshot of Kel, it was
overheard, and Kel came back
down.
>> KEITH: Hey, Kel.
>> KEL: How you doing?
>> KEITH: Good. How are you?
>> KEL: Good.
Hey.
Hey, guys?
>> MARALYN: Did you find
anything?
>> KEL: How are you guys doing?
>> MARALYN: Did you find
anything?
>> KEL: Just a second, just a
second.
How are you guys doing?
Look, while I was going up there
looking for bait for fishing,
you guys were talking about that
you thought I was eating beef
jerky...
That was a blade of grass, and I
smooshed it up into my jaw, and
I was chewing on that.
I was just chewing grass.
>> JERRI: Well, in order to put
grass in your mouth, you have to
go get grass first.
And I don't think you get grass
out of your pocket.
>> KEL: Just chewing a piece...
>> JERRI: What kind of grass?
>> KEL: Green grass.
Just any kind of grass you can
pick up.
>> AMBER: How do you know it's
not poisonous?
>> KEL: Uh, I mean, it looks...
it looks like normal grass,
okay?
It just looks like a normal
blade of grass, so I mean...
>> KEITH: We don't need you, uh,
sick at these competitions.
>> KEL: Well, I want to just
make sure that you guys know
that.
I'm really trying to be a part
of this group.
It's really important for me to
try to assimilate.
I may not be the most talkative
one in here, I'm a fairly quiet
person...
>> JERRI: Mm...
>> KEITH: Well, thanks for
coming and telling us.
>> JERRI: Yeah, we appreciate
the explanation.
>> KEL: No problem.
>> JERRI: We're-we're just, you
know, when someone's chewing
something and nobody else is and
everybody's starving.
>> KEL: Well, I just find it
really comical that you would
think I would do that.
>> MARALYN: I think it's pretty
comical...
>> KEL: I think it's... I think
it's comical myself.
( scattered chuckling )
And that also brings up another
point-- I was going to do this
later on tonight.
I know during the competition,
you guys were talking about your
faces were getting scruffy, and
the girls were talking about
wanting to shave their legs.
I've got three blades out here.
The girls can use one blade, the
guys can use the other blade.
I have no problem with that
whatsoever.
>> JERRI: He suddenly, at that
point, offered his razor.
And I think that that's the
hugest sign of guilt is to give
to the people who have just
accused you of something that is
very serious.
>> JERRI: I will totally take
you up on that.
That's very gracious of you,
actually.
>> KEL: No problem.
Sorry for the awkward moment.
I will now leave you guys in
peace, and I'll go in my boat
and try finding some kind of
fish with the bait I have.
>> MARALYN: I suggested to them
all, "Hey, what you all did was
totally inappropriate.
It was wrong.
Nobody had any right to go into
Kel's bag."
I said, "Don't you think that it
would be in the best interest of
the team to be big enough to
apologize to him?"
Without real proof, it would be
very big of us to apologize.
>> JERRI: No.
>> MARALYN: Okay.
They said, "No. No."
( laughter )
>> JERRI: I think-I think
Maralyn is kind of upset at us.
>> MARALYN: Gee whiz, four days,
things are heating up at our
encampment.
>> NICK: It's on a bone.
>> ALICIA: Oh, boy.
>> NICK: "Want to try a new
dish?
Take care what you wish.
Next challenge may go too far.
Just say 'Rub-A-Dub-Dub,' thank
God for the grub.
Close your eyes, plug your nose
and swallow hard."
We're eating...
>> ALICIA: We're eating bugs.
>> NICK: We're eating something
crazy.
>> ALICIA: We got this one.
We're eating bugs.
>> NICK: We're eating something.
>> ELISABETH: We should have
just been really hungry this
morning.
>> MICHAEL: Food is food, right?
>> KIMMI: What kind of bug?
>> MICHAEL: It's a worm.
>> ALICIA: It's grub.
>> JEFF V.: It's grub.
It's a worm.
>> NICK: You guys want to hear
it?
>> ALICIA: You guys ready to
hear this?
It's on a bone.
>> KIMMI: Our immunity challenge
came to us and it's something
about rub-a-dub-dub, we're
eating a grub or something.
( disgusted grunt )
Let me go last.
I'm a vegetarian, which means I
don't eat land-dwelling animals.
I'm not going to compromise my,
you know, situation, um, now.
>> I'm not eating amphibian.
I'm not eating reptile.
I'm not eating mammal.
I'm not eating foul.
>> ALICIA: Kimmi's not going to
compromise her morals, but
coming into a game like this,
you can't come in with a whole
list of things you're not going
to do and you're not going to
eat because you're not helping
your tribe, you're not helping
your team morale.
( disgusted groan )
>> MICHAEL: If Rodger can jump
off a cliff and swim that long
distance and down the rapids
with never having swum before, I
think Kimmi should be able to
reach down and be able to do
this.
>> JEFF V.: Oh, my God.
>> KIMMI: You know what?
I can't do it, and I'm
disappointing six people that
are rooting for me.
Now, you know, I have no excuse
for-for not being, um, voted off
the island.
I could be gone, just like that.
>> JEFF: I'll take the immunity
idol.
It's back up for grabs.
I'll explain the game.
I know you guys are hungry so
we've put together one of the
finest samplings of true
Aboriginal food, what they call
bush tucker.
As you guys know, the
Aboriginals have lived out here
for thousands of years,
literally by eating everything.
Nothing goes to waste.
Here's how it's going to work.
One member from each tribe will
come up.
I'll spin the wheel, and you'll
eat what's on here.
Also on the wheel, some treats
that might go down a little
easier.
If you're lucky, maybe you'll
get the fruit or the candy bar.
Since Kucha is short one member,
one of your members will have to
eat twice.
So whoever you select to go
first, will also eat last.
Now if you pass, and you don't
eat or you can't finish, you
lose a point.
At the end of one round, whoever
has the most points get the
immunity idol.
Losers lose another member
at tomorrow night's Tribal
Council.
Going down and coming back up
doesn't count.
It's got to stay down.
And the way you know is you show
me your mouth.
I look in, I don't see anything,
I'll say good to go.
This the mangrove worm.
It lives in little mangrove
trees.
It usually burrows a small hole
in its infancy stage, and then
as it grows, the hole gets
deeper and deeper and deeper,
sort of like a termite.
What are you taking out?
>> MARALYN: I'm ready.
>> JEFF: You're taking out your
teeth.
( scattered chuckling )
Mad Dog has just taken out her
teeth.
>> MICHAEL: Oh, my God.
JEFF: Here we go, guys.
Three, two, one.
You're on.
>> AMBER: Go, Maralyn.
>> JEFF: Let's see.
Good.
( Maralyn choking )
>> KEL: Come on, Maralyn.
>> JERRI: You can do it.
You can do it.
It's an oyster. It's an oyster.
>> JEFF: Got a bucket if you
need it, Maralyn.
>> MARALYN: Water?
>> JERRI: You got it.
( Maralyn choking )
It's all right.
( Maralyn puffing )
>> JERRI: Yeah!
( whooping )
>> MARALYN: Oh!
>> JEFF: Next two.
( Kimmi yells )
>> KIMMI: Brain.
>> JEFF: You got cow brain
there.
The good news is it's pretty
fresh.
It should have a nice taste to
it.
You guys ready for this?
>> KEITH: Sure.
>> JEFF: Three, two, one.
We're on.
>> KIMMI: I can't.
I can't eat a brain.
>> KEITH: Can we have some to
take back to camp with us?
>> MITCHELL: Yeah, Keith.
>> AMBER: You are the man.
>> MITCHELL: You the man.
>> KIMMI: I can't do it.
>> JEFF: Taking a pass, Kimmi?
>> KIMMI: It's a mammal.
I can't do it.
Sorry.
>> JEFF: Okay.
Let's see your mouth.
You're good.
Ogakor is one up.
>> AMBER: Yeah, Keith.
Next two.
That's mud whelk.
It's the shellfish you find
seaside.
Three, two, one.
We're on.
>> AMBER: Oh, that's nice.
>> COLBY: Atta-girl.
>> AMBER: That's it.
>> COLBY: Just swallow it.
>> NICK: You've got to savor it.
>> JEFF: Kind of crunchy, huh,
Jerri?
>> JERRI: Mmm.
>> JEFF V.: Let's get that thing
down, Nick.
>> ALICIA: Yeah, yeah.
No, no, no, hold it, hold it,
hold it. Hold it.
>> JEFF: I'll give you five
seconds.
Five, four, three, two, one.
>> AMBER: Come on, Jerri.
>> JEFF: Look at that.
( Jerri screams happily )
>> MARALYN: All right!
( Maralyn yells happily )
>> JEFF: Next two.
Kel and Elisabeth.
You got the apple.
>> MARALYN: Wow!
>> KEL: Yeah! Yeah!
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
( scattered chuckles )
>> JEFF: Next two.
>> MARALYN: Whatever it is, you
got it.
>> JEFF: That is witchety grub
larva.
This will become a moth.
It's in its early stages.
Ogakor you got a lead.
Three, two, one.
>> JERRI: Go.
Come on, Mitchell.
Go, Mitchell, go, Mitchell.
( laughing and cheering )
>> KEITH: Way to go, all right!
>> JEFF: Here we go.
>> JERRI: You can do it, Amber.
>> ALICIA: Ah! You suck.
>> JEFF: The pincers, you can
break off.
Everything else, you're eating.
Three, two, one.
>> TINA: Eat it little by
little, if you have to.
( indistinct talking )
>> COLBY: There you go.
All right.
>> Chips. Potato chips.
Ranch potato chips.
( indistinct talking )
>> JERRI: You got it.
>> COLBY: Okay, you got it.
>> RODGER: Swallow, swallow.
>> JEFF V.: Yeah!
>> MARALYN: Don't... don't think
about what's going through your
head right now.
It's a mental picture.
( cheering )
>> KEITH: All right.
>> COLBY: Yeah!
( indistinct talking )
>> JEFF: Here we go, guys.
>> COLBY Big bucks, big bucks.
No whammies.
Ooh.
Get past that.
( cheering )
>> JEFF: It's a candy bar.
Life is working for you guys.
>> MITCHELL: Go ahead, man.
Enjoy it.
We're with you in spirit.
>> JEFF: Last two.
Tina, Michael, you're up again.
Here's where we're at.
Kimmi passed, therefore, Kucha
is down one point.
Tina, if you swallow this last
one, your team wins immunity.
But if you don't and Michael
swallows his, we have a tie.
This is it, for immunity.
>> Perfect. Yeah.
>> JEFF: You got tripe, a cow's
stomach lining.
>> AMBER: Oh, Tina, that's the
best one.
>> JERRI: Steak. That's a steak.
>> AMBER: That's a steak.
>> RODGER: That's a sirloin.
>> JEFF: Three, two, one.
We're on.
>> JERRI: Prime rib, baby.
Prime rib.
Prime rib, prime rib.
>> JEFF: It's chewier than you
would expect.
>> JERRI: It's prime rib.
( indistinct talking )
>> KEL: It's okay, Tina.
>> JEFF: Okay?
>> JERRI: You're good, Tina,
you're good.
( gagging sound )
>> You're getting protein.
>> NICK: Slimy cow...
>> AMBER: Cover your mouth.
>> JEFF: You got a bucket, you
got a bucket.
It came up.
>> NICK: It came up.
( Tina retching )
>> It's all right.
No thing, no big thing.
>> TINA: Oh, sorry, guys.
( cheering )
>> JEFF: All right, guys, here's
how the tiebreaker is going to
work.
Ogakor, you select a member from
Kucha.
Kucha, you select your member
from Ogakor.
>> ALICIA: Tina's up.
>> JEFF: Tina?
>> JEFF: Right here, Kimmi?
>> Kimmi.
>> JEFF: Kimmi.
Your challenge is going to be to
take a whole mangrove worm.
>> ALICIA: This is all you,
girl.
>> JEFF: The first person to
completely swallow it, show me
their mouth, that it's empty,
wins.
( all talking at once )
>> KIMMI: I can eat a worm.
I can eat a worm.
>> JEFF: Three, two, one.
Go.
>> ALICIA: Swallow the whole
thing.
>> Pick it up.
>> TINA: She dropped it.
>> Eat it, eat it.
>> You got it.
( all talking at once )
( cheering )
>> JEFF: Kimmi, come here.
Immunity for Kucha.
( cheering )
>> TINA: I'll definitely feel
bad about having to vote
somebody off.
There's some humiliation
involved with being the first
one voted off.
>> You know, it's a bittersweet
opportunity.
Actually, it's a bitter
There is no sweetness to it.
We have to eliminate a person
within our group.
It could be me.
I mean, it really could be me.
For all I know, I could be the
individual going.
>> MITCHELL: Keith is, um, he's
a bit bossy.
He's very condescending, and
he's definitely... close to
going.
>> COLBY: If you were looking to
paint a bull's-eye on someone,
obviously Keith has struck a
nerve in a few people.
But also Jerri.
She's certainly, um, a very
strong girl and very set in her
ways.
>> JERRI: Really?
>> COLBY: And sometimes a little
unforgiving in certain areas.
>> JERRI: No, no, no, no.
We're going to talk right now.
>> COLBY: So that kind of makes
her a point of friction to some
people.
>> MARALYN: Some things that,
uh, that she's done have really
made me... me bristle.
( Jerri laughing )
>> KEL: At this point I'm going
to vote for Jerri.
And the reason why I'm going to
vote for Jerri is because I've
already told Maralyn that I was
going to do that, and I'm not
going to break my word.
And Maralyn told me she was
going to vote for Jerri, too.
And I trust Maralyn.
>> JERRI: I think Kel is a liar
and a cheat.
As much as I don't want to
believe that to be the truth,
he would probably be the first
one I would want to vote off.
>> AMBER: I'm ready to go.
>> MITCHELL: I think the name of
the game is trust no one.
I don't think you could trust
your own grandparents out here.
I mean, I think I would vote
them right off just 'cause
they've been married for 50
years.
That's a good alliance.
>> KEITH: This game is all about
deceit, deception and how to
play using your mind to win.
>> JEFF: All right, guys, we
begin Tribal Council with a
ritual.
I would like you to go ahead and
grab a torch... and approach the
flame.
Dip your torches in, and once
they're lit, you can put them
back in their slot.
We do this because fire does
represent life.
These torches will now represent
your life, your identity at
Tribal Council.
I haven't had a chance to talk
to you guys at Tribal Council
yet, so just a few questions
before we get to the vote.
You have fire.
You have a professional chef.
You guys should be eating very
well.
>> KEITH: You know what, until
we start really sourcing great
products to work with, our
creative juices are semi-limited
and stuff.
But we realized earlier we had
flour, and Jerri is a phenomenal
cook, so she steps in and she's
made tortillas.
We've had those for breakfast
every morning.
When we're done, we have Jerri's
tortillas shop opening up.
>> JEFF: Why are you cooking if
he's the chef?
( Jerri sighs )
>> JERRI: I knew you were going
to go there.
( laughs )
The rice was a little pasty the
first couple of nights, and it
got to the point where none of
us wanted to eat it, and that's
when I felt I needed to step in
because we were losing strength.
Our morale was down.
I mean, when you don't want to
even eat, that's a really bad
sign of bad things to come.
So I just took it upon myself.
>> JEFF: Colby, what was your
reaction to Keith's food?
>> COLBY: Oh, I had no problem
with it.
Rice is rice, man.
>> MARALYN: Jeff... if it-if it
goes down and doesn't come back
up, it's a good meal.
>> KEL: Exactly.
>> JEFF: That's what we found
out yesterday.
( Amber and Jerri groaning )
Tina, what's been your lowest
low?
>> TINA: Probably throwing up
that intestines that I ate and
feeling like I let my team down.
>> JEFF: So let me ask you the
question that is most on my
mind: Do you feel like you need
to say, "I know I screwed up,
but guys, here's why you should
keep me"?
>> TINA: Absolutely not.
I feel like I-I'm the one who
screwed up, I should be the
one to go.
>> JEFF: Having said that, it is
time to vote.
Jerri, you're first.
>> Nothing against you, Jerri,
but I already promised Tina and
Maralyn that I would not vote
against them, and I would vote
for you.
I made this on day one, and I
don't break my promises.
Sorry about that, Jerri.
>> MITCHELL: As much as we could
use your strength in our
challenges, we're a little sick
and tired of some of your games.
The only comfort I have in
voting this way is the fact that
you brought this on all by
yourself.
I'm sorry.
>> MARALYN: Kel.
Kel, if you were lying in the
Simpson Desert, dying of thirst,
every single one of us would
give you a drink of water.
Good luck to you.
>> JEFF: Once the votes are
tallied, the decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
along this bridge.
The first vote...
Kel.
Jerri.
That's three votes for Kel, one
for Jerri.
Four votes Kel.
The first person voted out of
the Ogakor tribe...
Kel.
Kel, I need you to bring your
torch.
Kel, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, you survived Tribal
Council number one.
You have a long walk home.
Go ahead and grab your torches
and head back to camp.
See you tomorrow.
>> Stay tuned for scenes from
our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
Jerri makes her move on Colby.
>> JERRI: He's a cowboy, and I'm
such a sucker for cowboys.
( Cobly moans )
>> COLBY: Just two school kids
on the playground having fun.
>> At Kucha, Michael is obsessed
with making a kill...
>> MICHAEL: This is a pig
killer.
>> ...causing tempers to flare.
>> That stupid spear.
That's classic Mike.
He's an idiot.
( Michael laughing )
>> KEL: I knew right from day
one that it was going to be hard
for me to fit in.
I'm a military guy, and the
people I was working with are
very unique special type of
people.
It was going to be very hard for
me to fit into that mixture.
I tried, I really did.
But I don't think in a couple of
days I could have overcome our
differences.
Good luck.
You're all winners to me.