>> JEFF: Previously on
Survivor, Keith and Tina
plotted to take down Jerri.
>> TINA: She's the most bossy,
domineering person I've ever
met.
>> KEITH: I didn't come out here
to be pushed around by a
bartender-wannabe-actress.
>> JEFF: Jerri persuaded Colby
to make a deal.
>> COLBY: It's me, you and
Amber, through to the end.
>> JERRI: It's not like you're
making a deal with the devil
here.
>> COLBY: I simply agreed to go
along with them to get me down
the road a little better.
>> JEFF: Kimmi's morals were
compromised when the tribe won
chickens in a reward challenge.
>> KIMMI: Don't break her wings,
though.
Can't they give us some edamame,
some tofu...?
>> JEFF: Michael shocked his
tribe by killing a pig.
>> KIMMI: We live in a sick
tribe.
>> ELISABETH: We're going to get
strong now.
>> JEFF: Kucha continued their
winning streak by taking the
immunity challenge, sending
Ogakor back to Tribal Council
for the third consecutive time,
where the vote was deadlocked in
a double tie between Keith and
Mitchell.
One vote is the difference.
But ultimately it was Mitchell
who was voted out, putting a
dent in Jerri's hopes for an
alliance.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( birds chirping )
>> COLBY: We really started
noticing the smoke and hearing
the trees explode and crash.
Uh, yesterday, I guess, is when
it got the closest to us.
And now we're just completely
pretty much overtaken by smoke.
>> AMBER: My eyes are watering.
>> TINA: It's just extremely
hazy and smoky, and...
It's an interesting morning.
>> AMBER: We've had an
interesting past couple of days,
as far as, uh...
Let's see, our last Tribal
Council we lost Mitchell, which
was a surprise.
>> JERRI: It was a pretty...
pretty traumatic evening.
I think our little group of
common voters has been busted
up.
It's a whole new ball game right
now.
>> KEITH: Love this game.
>> JERRI ( half-whispering ):
Tina and Keith are definitely
grouped together, but Colby is
like the one in the middle,
like...
>> AMBER: They're totally
grouping together.
>> JERRI: Everybody else is
trying to pair up, or they're
trying...
We're all vying for Colby's
vote.
>> COLBY: I'm playing from the
center, dude.
I'm playing from...
( Keith laughing )
Let's squash this one.
>> AMBER: Seems like since Tina
was able to get Colby to sway
his vote last time and vote for
Mitchell, seems like maybe he,
uh, might sway again to their
side.
But we're almost kind of
fighting over him.
>> COLBY: What we did was
strategic, and it was to help
the team out, and I know it did
that.
>> JERRI: I have, you know...
I'm not harboring any ill
feelings whatsoever about the
whole deal.
We still are more powerful if
the three of us are voting the
same.
>> COLBY: I'm still voting just
like I did last night, based on
who the strongest... who I
think's got what it takes to
make it in.
Maybe tomorrow, I might be
thinking a whole lot different,
but... right now I'm not.
>> JERRI: I mean, it's basically
the end of any alliance, pretty
much.
>> COLBY: Jerri, I don't care.
I don't care about that stage of
it.
I mean, all I care about is
doing everything we can to win
the next two immunity
challenges.
That's the only thing I can
focus on right now.
>> KIMMI: Good morning,
stinkies.
We gotta clean you out, 'cause
you all stink.
Last night was a very
uncomfortable sleeping night.
It was drafty, it was cold.
Nobody slept last night.
Like, it was just like one of
those nights where anything and
everything that could wake you
up did.
>> JEFF V.: I woke up once, and
there was a hot coal on my
shirt-- look.
>> RODGER: You're kidding?
>> JEFF V.: And there was a
little fire in my wooly.
>> NICK: Whew!
>> ALICIA: "Fire in my woolly."
That's not the first time I
heard that.
Well, how the hell did it
bypass everybody else in front
of you?
>> JEFF V.: I don't know, but if
it came all the way back here,
it could have landed on your
face.
>> MICHAEL: That's exactly
right.
>> JEFF V.: Know what I'm
saying?
>> ALICIA: That's not funny.
>> JEFF V.: It's not funny.
The fire had been popping coals
out of the fire onto us.
>> ALICIA: Wow.
>> JEFF V.: So, we had to move
our fire this morning.
It just was getting a little too
dangerous.
>> KIMMI: Very good chickens.
They're very happy now.
Hello, hello...
>> JEFF V.: We got fire!
>> RODGER: It was a little
inconvenient right there, you
know, but boy, late at night,
nighttime, be...
Gonna be different around there
when it gets cold at night.
I guess we're ready to go.
Chicken killing time.
>> ALICIA: You know what,
though?
That hatchet needs to be
sharpened.
It's pretty dull again.
>> RODGER: Mike got the pig,
and, uh, we ate real good.
We wasn't able to save all the
meat, so I guess we're going to
eat chicken.
So, we won't have the eggs.
( scraping continues )
Sharp as possible while we're...
while we're doing the chicken
in.
>> KIMMI: Hello, ladies.
I have such brilliant hens over
here, yes...
>> MICHAEL: I just tell Kimmi,
"For your own self-preservation,
let go of the chicken thing.
Stop talking about them, stop
getting involved..."
>> KIMMI: What's going over
>> NICK: We're building a fire
to boil water, to kill the
chicken.
( clucking )
>> KIMMI: Well, that's my cue.
>> MICHAEL: Yeah, we're ready.
>> KIMMI: See you later, bye.
>> MICHAEL: Stop making a big
spectacle when you leave.
"Oh, you're butchering the
chickens, I'm out of here!"
Da-da-da-da-da!
You know, I mean, it's just...
It's too theatrical, it's just
too much.
>> KIMMI: Bye, chickies,
bye-bye.
>> MICHAEL: I'm ready.
I'm feeling the need to shed
some blood.
>> ALICIA: Whatever.
( indistinct voices )
>> RODGER: I don't... I don't, I
don't enjoy killing animals,
neither.
>> ELISABETH: Sure.
>> RODGER: I don't, really, but
sometimes, nobody wants to do
it.
Jeff, you want to do it?
>> MICHAEL: I thought Jeff
wanted to do it.
>> ELISABETH: Maybe next time.
>> RODGER: You got it?
( pounding, moaning )
>> ELISABETH: I like that.
Get these feathers off.
>> JEFF V.: Oh, they're hot.
>> RODGER: Yeah, this is by far
the right...
>> ELISABETH: Good stuff.
That chicken's going to be so
awesome...
>> ALICIA: It's gonna be so
good.
( indistinct voices )
>> AMBER: Thank you.
>> KEITH: You're welcome.
>> AMBER: The food situation
could definitely be better.
It could always get better.
We're not eating that much at
all.
We're definitely not eating as
much as the other tribe is.
>> JERRI: When you come to see
me, we have to go somewhere and
get a really good pizza.
>> AMBER: Okay.
>> JERRI: And lots of garlic and
bread...
We haven't caught any fish for,
I think, two days now.
The whole hunger thing, that for
me has been a huge hurdle.
Keith, did you disassemble some
of these for the line the other
night?
The only ones that are rigged to
go are the cricket and the
silver one.
>> KEITH: Jerri went to go
fishing, and she needed the can.
And of course, she hollered out
to me, like her older sibling.
>> JERRI: What do you suggest we
do with the fish guts?
>> KEITH: I said we'll take them
to the end and dump them in the
water, like we've been doing it.
And so, she brought them down to
the water's edge down at the end
of camp to dump them out, and
then she yelled back that it's
not a smart idea to dump them in
there, because...
>> JERRI: We're literally
feeding the fish every time we
dump the guts down there.
>> KEITH: Well, my vote is you
just bury them in the sand down
by the end down there.
>> JERRI: The thing is, it's
also downwind from us, so once
they start rotting, if by chance
you get a second, if you want
to...
>> KEITH: I'll bury them.
>> JERRI: Yeah?
>> KEITH: No problem.
>> JERRI: That would be really
cool.
>> KEITH: It's all right.
I'm thinking on these couple
hundred acres of water, I'm not
sure that a few fish eating some
dead fish is going to matter a
whole lot, but whatever.
>> JERRI: It's just ridiculous
to me to continue to dump the
guts at the end of our beach.
We're literally feeding the
fish.
It's no wonder we haven't been
able to catch anything, they're
all full.
>> KEITH: It's not that big of a
deal, but apparently...
it was.
I don't stand up to her that
often, 'cause I don't find it
necessary, 'cause it's more
exhausting to argue with her
than anything.
The fish... are now... buried.
Dead fish.
>> JERRI: We haven't been
catching fish again, and the
other team is eating chickens
and pigs and eggs, you know.
And here we are over here,
starving to death.
>> KEITH: You have any?
>> JERRI: No luck.
Those are the things that I
didn't really think going into
this that were going to bother
me.
But it has.
>> KIMMI: ...something really
different.
>> ALICIA: No, no, I didn't get
upset about you; I left.
>> KIMMI: No, my point is, is
that with the, uh, chicken, I'm
just saying for these guys to
stay stronger, it's better to,
like, do every other day,
putting meat in their body.
>> ALICIA: You gotta be kidding?
>> KIMMI: I don't know.
>> ALICIA: We're active every
day, we need protein every day.
>> KIMMI: No, my points is...
>> ALICIA: That's not a good
argument, it's not gonna work.
>> KIMMI: This isn't like a
debate to be arguing about.
>> ALICIA: No, I know.
>> KIMMI: I'm just saying...
>> ALICIA: But I'm telling you
why I don't agree with you.
That's exactly the point.
>> KIMMI: Okay, well, you don't
have to agree with me.
>> ALICIA: And I don't.
So, there you go.
>> KIMMI: Okay, fine.
>> ALICIA: I'm tired of the
chickens, tired of it.
>> KIMMI: Excuse me?
>> ALICIA: Do you have some kind
of a problem?
>> KIMMI: Yeah, I have a problem
with your attitude.
>> ALICIA: Oh really!?
>> KIMMI: What the hell is up
your butt?
>> ALICIA: What you just said is
not true.
We should be having protein
every day.
If we have to have the chickens,
we will.
>> KIMMI: I'm just saying, if
you had the chickens here...
>> ALICIA: Right!
You see us going fishing, right?
>> KIMMI: You can go...
That's all I was saying-- it's a
good just thing to break it up,
especially...
>> ALICIA: You are the defensive
one about the chickens, not me,
so do not yell at me about the
chickens.
>> KIMMI: I am not getting
emotionally attached.
>> ALICIA: You can get as
emotionally attached as you
want.
Because the only reason why we
said it is 'cause we care about
your feelings 'cause you're part
in this tribe.
But don't jump all over me,
sweetheart, don't ever...
>> KIMMI: But the thing is, I'm
not getting upset.
Don't wave your finger in my
face.
>> ALICIA: I will always wave my
finger...
>> KIMMI: And mumble under your
breath.
>> ALICIA: You want me to say it
to your face?
>> KIMMI: Yes, if you have...
>> ALICIA: Yes, I will be happy
to.
I'm saying it to your face right
now.
>> KIMMI: Thank you!
>> ALICIA: I'm tired of you and
the... chickens-- you heard it!
>> KIMMI: What have I said about
the chickens, though?
Nothing! That's the problem.
>> ALICIA: Please, you and your
little...
( didgeridoo playing )
>> KIMMI: She has more of an
issue with the chickens than I
do.
Gosh!
>> ALICIA: I don't really
appreciate her to begin with, so
for me to try to walk away from
a situation I know is
potentially going to turn ugly,
and her not to let me do that,
made me want to just run up and
grab her by the throat.
But I-I had to keep my wits
about me, because that's not
what this is about.
>> JEFF V.: What did I just
miss? I was peeing?
>> ALICIA: Plenty.
I've never liked Kimmi, we all
know that.
So when she jumps on me, I will
go at her guns loaded, okay?
>> JEFF V.: What did she say,
though?
I totally missed it.
What happened?
>> ALICIA: Sitting on the floor
of the house, she goes...
>> KIMMI: Alicia has always had
a problem with me.
She said, "Kimmi, don't get too
attached to the chickens."
I'm like, "I'm not getting
Like, don't worry!
I'm a big girl.
I said, "You know, while we have
the chickens here we shouldn't
just eat four chickens and a pig
back-to-back days.
>> ALICIA: I said, "You know
what, Kimmi?
This is why we didn't want you
to get emotionally attached to
the chickens."
That's all I said.
>> KIMMI: She's very critical of
other people, she's very
condescending of other people,
and I will not be treated, um,
you know, like a jerk-off.
>> ALICIA ( scoffing ): Give me
a break.
If you're going to make sense,
you can say whatever you want to
me, but if you're not going to
make sense, keep your mouth
shut.
>> JEFF V.: I knew that that
Alicia/Kimmi explosion was
coming, I knew it was coming.
Kimmi was befriending the
chickens and giving them names
and petting them.
And, um, Alicia just has no
patience.
Alicia doesn't have a lot of
patience for anybody, really.
>> ALICIA: I had enough, and I
let loose, baby.
>> ELISABETH: Alicia is in
charge of telling people to do
things.
Alicia is also in charge of
talking trash about people.
>> ALICIA: We still have to stay
together as a team.
>> ELISABETH: We do.
>> ALICIA: So I'm willing to
live and let live.
>> KIMMI: I just think it was a
silly misunderstanding.
But we all are on the same team,
so we gotta... at least have a
poker face on for game day, I
suppose.
( birds squawking )
>> NICK: This fire doesn't throw
off the heat that the other fire
did.
>> ALICIA: This is the only
time, though, when the fire
really stinks, you know...
>> NICK: We moved the fire pit
away from our camp for some
safety reasons.
And we had it nice and close--
about five feet from where we
all sleep, so it was really warm
at night.
But we moved it away, and last
night was really, really cold.
>> RODGER: Coldest night for me.
Whew!
>> NICK: You know, what can we
do?
We don't have any blankets, so
then we just bundle up.
>> ALICIA: Come on over to the
fire.
>> RODGER: Cold on that
outside...
>> MICHAEL: Let me tell you, it
was cold on the inside, so if it
was cold on the inside...
>> RODGER: Oh...
>> KIMMI: The water here grosses
me out more than anything.
This Crocodile Creek is food and
bathroom to fish and crocodiles
and birds and bats, and, you
know all kinds of algae and
bacteria.
And it's just... I don't know, I
just find it to be incredibly
gross.
>> MICHAEL: Kimmi, I don't know
if she's been in the water once,
and... the dirt's starting to
stick to her.
>> KIMMI: But also 'cause you
can see my tan line-- look at
it.
>> MICHAEL: You know, some, one
of the other girls puts on a
different top, you'll see a tan
line.
When Kimmi puts on a different
top, you'll see a dirt line.
>> KIMMI: I washed yesterday.
>> MICHAEL: You changed clothes.
I mean, your neck is, like,
filthy.
>> KIMMI: Filthy, well be...
Oh, because I was carrying tree
stuff today.
That's why my neck is filthy.
>> MICHAEL: And then she got
real defensive about it.
I said "I'm..." I said, "If I
had a booger hanging out of my
nose, and you told me about it,
I would say 'thank you.'
I wouldn't get all mad at you."
>> KIMMI: That's nice.
>> MICHAEL: I mean, it's not
bad.
I mean, we're all dirty.
>> RODGER: Whew!
>> ELISABETH: It's a big one!
>> NICK: Is it FedEx?
>> ELISABETH: Feels like a
package.
>> NICK: Wow.
>> ELISABETH: It's a book!
>> NICK: It's a catalog.
>> ELISABETH: Check this thing
out!
>> MICHAEL: That is stylin'!
>> KIMMI: Wow!
>> ELISABETH: Okay, "You must be
prepared when your tribe's in a
bind.
Build a travois, and save their
behinds..."
>> JEFF V.: Build a what?
>> ELISABETH: Build a tra...
>> NICK: A stretcher thing.
>> ELISABETH: Like a stretcher
"...and save their behinds.
Look through this book.
You can only choose two.
Plus from your friends at
Target...
clean teeth and shampoo!"
>> KIMMI: Shampoo! Oh!
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God, you
guys!
>> NICK: We get to pick two
things, we get to pick two
things.
>> ELISABETH: Okay, boxers and
slippers?
>> KIMMI: No.
>> ELISABETH: We'll skip that
page.
Toilet paper?
>> NICK: Blankets, we need
blankets.
>> ELISABETH: Blankets I think
is one, don't you?
>> RODGER: Blankets would be...
>> ALICIA: Blankets would be
wonderful, 'cause we really--
now that we moved our fire...
>> MICHAEL: I think we're all...
>> ALICIA: ...we really have an
issue with that.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah.
>> RODGER: Everybody wants the
spices?
>> ELISABETH: Oh, it is a
catalog...
>> RODGER: Raise your hand.
Everybody wants spices who...
what do you want?
Spices? I'll go with spices.
>> ELISABETH: The two items that
we chose... we definitely need
blankets.
Last night was really cold.
I had a miserable night's sleep.
I don't know if anyone really
slept through, especially
without our fire out here, it's
so cold.
We are going to choose for the
second item spices, and we get
toothpaste and shampoo when we
win this today.
>> ALICIA: "Travois."
They're using some French words.
>> NICK: A stretcher.
>> ALICIA: It's a stretcher, to
carry somebody in.
>> MICHAEL: Look how they show
the thing, though.
It's not like what you'd think.
It's a teepee... it's a
triangle.
>> ALICIA: Yeah, it's a tri...
>> ELISABETH: Wow!
>> NICK: We have to make one of
these, you guys.
So, how are we going to build
this thing?
Let's think.
>> KIMMI: Yes?
>> ALICIA: We could even make
something out of rope for her
feet to sit in.
>> ELISABETH: We could have add-
ins, like a pillow...
>> RODGER: If we use that bamboo
pole, how are we going to tie
onto that?
>> ALICIA: Those up there are
going to start to cross.
>> KIMMI: Is that real hard
wood?
>> ELISABETH: That can go right
under my butt.
>> JEFF V.: That's the width.
We want the length.
>> MICHAEL: Keep it tight where
you guys had it, at the top.
>> RODGER: Can you come around
this and tie a bunch of
slipknots in?
>> ELISABETH: Is that on your
head?
>> KIMMI: Yeah, but that's okay.
>> ALICIA: We're gonna need it
for the back corner...
>> RODGER: Are your legs still
where you can reach the corners?
Or you need to slide down a
little bit?
>> ALICIA: Rock solid.
>> MICHAEL: One, two, lift.
( Elisabeth laughs )
>> ALICIA: Feels stable enough?
>> KIMMI: Mm-hmm.
>> ELISABETH: Whee!
>> RODGER: All right, we got it
down.
>> ELISABETH: I think over at,
uh, Ogakor, they're probably
trying to pull it together
really well.
We have to go out there as if
we're facing a tribe just as
strong as we are.
>> AMBER: Who's gonna decide do
we want to make it like a
rectangle...?
>> JERRI: All right, here, give
me the goods, then just hold...
You hold onto that end, and as I
weave it just follow-follow me
with this.
>> COLBY: We're dragging this
thing.
We want the least amount of
friction we can get.
>> JERRI: Okay, so what's your
point?
What's wrong with this?
>> COLBY: I'm saying...
>> JERRI: Do you see what I'm
doing with this, though?
>> COLBY: Exactly, and I think
it's great.
I'm saying instead of starting
it over the top, start it
underneath.
>> AMBER: From underneath.
>> COLBY: You see what I'm
saying?
>> KEITH: We got two pieces...
>> JERRI: No, I don't see what
you're saying.
You guys want to, like, put her
in it and pick it up-- the four
of us-- just to see what
happens?
I got kind of tickled when
making the travois.
I knew that the idea I had would
work, and everybody was just
kind of standing around and
talking.
And no one was doing anything.
So I just kind of grabbed the
bull by the horns.
God bless America... this...
>> KEITH: I have probably a
little more patience than Colby
does.
But I can usually tell when he's
getting a little tense and a
little agitated, you know.
He'll walk away from it and just
take a breath.
>> JERRI: Let's try it this way,
just in case we're able to.
>> AMBER: Is it really bad?
>> JERRI: Yay, it works!
>> TINA: Ooh!
>> JERRI: Oh!
>> COLBY: The toughest part for
this tribe is coming into these
challenges with our guns
blazing, ready to rock.
We gotta win this thing, and we
still got a shot at doing it.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
All right, well, we've already
established how tough it is
living in the Outback.
You're battling-- among other
things-- an out of control fire,
wildlife, crocodiles, snakes,
spiders.
If you get hurt, you are a long
way from help.
You have to be able to rely on
your tribe mates to get you back
to safety.
That's where today's challenge
comes in: triage.
You were asked to build a
travois-- a three-sided
stretcher.
You're going to use that today.
Two members from each tribe will
be the rescuers.
Three members will be the
victims.
You'll be placed at three
different spots out here on the
river on little sand spits.
There's a flag designating the
area.
There is a circle around that
flag.
The victims will stand inside
that circle.
When the rescuers get out there,
you get on your travois and you
head back.
Once they cross this line and
they're okay, they are
miraculously healed, they become
a rescuer.
Now you have three.
Going for the next person.
First tribe to get all three of
their victims back to the first
aid camp wins reward.
Now, Kucha, because you guys
have two extra members, two
people will sit out.
The winning tribe gets what they
wanted and also what the other
tribe wanted.
( all groaning )
>> ELISABETH: Shut up!
>> JEFF: So, Kucha, you chose
the blankets and the spices.
Ogakor, you also chose the
spaces and the soup mix.
>> ALICIA: It's a beautiful
thing.
>> JEFF: And Target has thrown
in a few other items.
They're not necessities, these
are luxuries.
Got fresh toothbrush...
( murmuring )
>> AMBER: Oh, my gosh!
>> JEFF ...toothpaste,
deodorant.
>> RODGER: Oh, yeah, we could
use that.
>> JEFF: And of course, what
every survivor needs, shampoo.
( all cheering )
>> ELISABETH: Wow!
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
>> ELISABETH: That's awesome.
>> JEFF: Okay, you guys decide
who is going to sit out.
Decide on your rescuers and your
victims.
Wait for my start.
>> TINA: Go, Ogakor!
Come on, guys!
>> JEFF: Kimmi and Rodger,
you're sitting out for Kucha.
A lot of reward at stake.
Survivors, ready...
Go!
>> TINA: Go, go, go, go!
>> Dude, come here.
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
Pick it up!
>> KIMMI: Go, Kucha!
>> ALICIA: Guys, push, push,
push, push, push!
Get ahead!
( team members yelling )
>> ELISABETH: Kucha!
>> JERRI: Ogakor!
( yelling, shouting )
>> RODGER: You're ahead!
>> MICHAEL: Walk through!
>> ELISABETH: Okay, okay.
>> Good job, Kucha!
>> RODGER: Good job, all right!
>> JEFF: Congratulations.
Nice job, Kucha.
>> It's all yours.
>> Good job.
>> JEFF: Here we go, guys.
>> NICK: Here's blankets.
>> RODGER: All right.
( happy shouting )
>> All right, all right.
>> AMBER: I'm just so tired of
losing.
( sniffling, crying )
>> TINA: Don't let 'em break
your spirit now.
>> COLBY: I am getting very
frustrated with losing.
If we don't turn up the heat and
turn this runaway train around,
then it may be a meltdown for
the Colbster.
>> TINA: It's not the things you
lose, it's just losing.
You know, it takes such a
psychological hit on your
already psychologically tired
body that, for our team, it's
definitely the loss that hits us
hard.
>> ALICIA: Winning the reward
challenges is, basically, just
one more nail in the coffin.
Not as important as immunity,
but another thing that's gonna
sink them just a little bit
lower.
>> JEFF V.: I don't mean to
sound evil, but it's all about
kicking somebody's ass.
>> ALICIA: There's no way
they're gonna give up.
They were very graceful losers,
actually.
I'm just so glad we're not them
right now.
That's rough.
>> JEFF V.: Some of the people
in the tribe are talking about
how guilty they feel and how bad
they feel for the other tribe--
and screw it!
I mean, chop their heads off,
chop their legs off, this is a
game and I'm ready to beat every
one of them.
I'm ready to chop their heads
off and their eyeballs out so
Mike can eat them...
( laughter )
>> JEFF V.: I stink.
>> ELISABETH: Me, too.
>> ALICIA: Toothpaste and
toothbrush and shampoo and
deodorant.
I'm not going to know what to do
with myself.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh!
Shampoo that doubles as soap.
>> JEFF V.: Let's go wash.
>> MICHAEL: Everybody else
smells out here, but everybody
else bathes.
Thank God we won that challenge,
so that we can bathe Kimmi.
>> MICHAEL: Group bath.
We won the reward challenge
yesterday and we used the
shampoo-- we each got a handful,
and we just all soaped up,
'cause the camp was getting a
little stinky.
Some more than others, because
some people bathe more than
others around here-- but it was
fun.
>> RODGER: You've got to prove
that.
( laughter )
>> AMBER: We got mail!
"This next challenge will prove
harder than the rest,
You'll be rats in the maze
for this little test.
Just keep your wits and
you'll make it with ease,
The prize is the idol and that's
much better than cheese."
>> JERRI: Oh, a maze!
>> AMBER: I think we should have
a little pep talk.
Well, I think... today, I don't
think it's our strength is going
to get us through this
challenge.
I honestly think it's our minds
and our hearts, and if we all
believe we can do it.
I definitely think we can.
So just make sure that you don't
doubt your heart and your mind
at all today, and I think that
will get us through it.
>> JERRI: There's a lot of
pressure on us today-- a lot.
But let's not forget also to
have fun with this.
>> COLBY: It is going to take
every ounce of keenness, of
smarts, of strength, of
everything we have.
The excuses are done, check them
at the door and let's get down
to business.
It is going to be one hell of a
show today and it's... you know,
I think we're as ready as we're
going to be.
>> JERRI: All right, Ogabkor.
Here we go!
Let's do this!
>> JEFF: I'll take that.
Once again, give it up, Varner.
The immunity idol is back up for
grabs.
Here's the deal today:
A giant maze.
46 tons of lumber, three miles
of burlap, two weeks to build.
Each maze is identical.
Inside each maze, five totem
poles-- attached to each totem
pole are these medallions.
They're numbered, one, two,
three, four, five.
Working as a unit, your goal
is to get through the maze,
collecting the medallions in
order.
One first, then two, then three.
If you find five first, don't
grab it.
Once you've collected all five,
get out of the maze on the other
side.
First tribe to the immunity
idol wins immunity.
It's about 110 degrees today.
Should work up a nice lather.
Kucha, because there's no
obvious advantage or
disadvantage to having more
members in this, you'll run the
full seven.
All right, we'll get going.
>> ALL: One, two, three, Ogakor!
>> ALL: Kucha!
>> JEFF: All right, immunity at
stake!
Survivors ready...
Go!
>> COLBY: Go back, go back.
>> TINA: Go back, go back.
>> KEITH: Dead end-- go back, go
back.
>> Straight-- this way.
>> NICK: I see one, I see one,
I just don't know how to get
there.
There's two.
There's two in the far right
corner.
Keep moving on--
this way, this way.
We all together?
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> COLBY: Work around to the
right.
>> Right here.
>> COLBY: Got it, got one.
Two is over there.
Go!
>> JEFF V.: No, it's right here.
One! One! One!
Okay, where was two?
>> Far right corner.
>> This way, this way!
No, to the left, this way.
>> I'm right here!
>> He's over here!
>> No, you're going nowhere!
It's this way!
>> Come here, come here.
Is somebody here?
>> COLBY: We found three.
>> No...
>> All right, it's got to be in
the back corner.
>> Back up?
>> Back, all the way in the
corner.
Go... come on.
>> Here we go, here we go, here
we go.
>> Jeff!
>> I got two right here.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Good job, good job.
>> Yeah, we lost three...
>> Three's back that way...
>> Go, go, go.
>> Other way-- right there.
>> Straight? Straight.
>> Right there.
>> KEITH: It's right in here.
Come back.
It's right here.
This... Right there.
Go around this way.
>> JERRI: That's three.
>> KEITH: Four is in the front
right corner, five is in the
middle.
Come on, Amber.
>> Go, Keith, go.
>> Go on, go on, go on, go on!
>> NICK: Mike, I think we got to
go all the way back down.
>> Yeah, that way.
>> Go all the way down...
( all talking )
>> JERRI: Come on, you guys,
we got it.
>> Left?
>> Yeah!
>> COLBY: I see it.
It's right there.
>> AMBER: Right here, guys!
>> Go, go, go, go.
All right, all right.
>> Yeah...
>> Go, go!
>> MICHAEL: I got it, I got it.
Got it, got it, got it.
No, no, no, right here.
It's right here.
We just gotta get there from
that way.
It's right there.
We got to get to it from
that side, though.
>> NICK: Can't we go around that
way?
>> AMBER: Where is it?
Here it is!
>> Go, go.
>> Which way?
>> It's that way...
This is it, this is it.
We gotta go.
>> COLBY: Tina, don't get lost!
Tina, Tina, come here!
>> TINA: Okay, I see your flag!
>> Come back, Tina.
>> No, dead end, dead end!
>> Turn around!
>> I'm right behind you!
>> Come on...
Come on!
>> I'm here, I'm here.
>> TINA: We're here.
>> Go, go!
>> TINA: We're out!
We're out!
>> Come on!
Go, go, go!
Hurry up!
( screaming )
>> COLBY: Yes!
( cheering, whooping )
>> JEFF: Yesterday, sitting in
the water, Amber, tears rolling
down your face, you said, "I'm
sick of losing."
>> AMBER: Do you see any tears
right now?
If they were, they'd be tears of
joy.
>> JEFF: Congratulations!
All right, guys, you can head
back.
Kucha, see you tonight at the
Tribal Council.
>> ALICIA: Exactly, that's the
only way.
>> JEFF V.: You get on my
nerves, and I don't care...
>> ALICIA: I know, sweetie.
>> JEFF V.: Stickin' to it.
We are not a happy tribe.
We are not the family we
appear to be.
There is some animosity.
>> ALICIA: She causes so much
trouble within the tribe, as
well.
>> JEFF V.: That's a name I'm
going to be happy to write down.
>> ALICIA: Yeah, me, too.
>> KIMMI: I'm sure Jeff and
Alicia are gonna vote together,
and you've been spending a lot
of time with them-- I figure you
guys are going to vote together,
>> MICHAEL: Who?
>> KIMMI: You, Alicia and Jeff.
>> MICHAEL: I'm not in their
pact.
I'm not in their thing.
>> ALICIA: Tribal Council is a
drag, no matter which way you
look at it.
It's clear-cut who should go,
but they stay a little longer
and then somebody steps up and
looks like they should go.
So, for me, Kimmi is a physical
weakness, and she just makes the
most sense right now, because I
have personal problems with her.
We just clash.
>> RODGER: It could be very
interesting, Tribal Council.
Right now, I assume that they
think that I'm voting against
Kimmi.
More than likely, that probably
will not be the case.
The only person that I keep my
word with out here is Elisabeth,
and I think she's the same way
towards me.
>> ELISABETH: I took a little
siesta and I said, it ticked me
off that you would just complain
to everyone else, and not say
something to Kimmi, just 'cause
you're afraid you'll get a vote.
I'm, like, if it's bothering you
that much, I don't want to hear
it, tell Kimmi.
>> RODGER: Mm-hmm.
In the boat today, we were
talking about voting against
Alicia.
And we would miss her, she does
a good job cooking, you know...
she's athletic... and, uh...
but there might be a little bit
more harmony around, too.
>> ELISABETH: Ready?
>> Let's go.
( thunder rumbling )
>> NICK: That thunder's coming
in.
>> RODGER: Don't like that.
>> JEFF: Welcome back.
I haven't really had a chance to
talk to you guys since Debb was
voted out in the first Tribal
Council.
Haven't been back.
Michael, last time you were
here, Rodger sort of, kind of
confirmed that you were sort of
the leader of the group.
Or you had taken that position.
>> MICHAEL: You know, everybody
has taken a leadership role in
this camp in one way, shape or
form.
It happened to be that food
seemed to be on the top of the
charts and I was bringing in
fish.
And so, you know, I possibly was
anointed the leader by Rodger
that day.
But everybody on this team has
contributed in their own way in
equal amount, and that's why
we've been so strong.
( thunder rumbles, rain falls )
>> JEFF: Well, as always, it
seems like when you guys are
here, we get the rain coming
down.
And there go the caps.
Alicia, talk to me about
leadership, because for me,
looking in, I would say you seem
to be a strong leader on this
tribe as well.
>> ALICIA: I don't know about
that.
I'm not so sure I'm a leader as
much as maybe a motivator.
I like to make sure that
everybody is on the same page.
I think if we're all on the same
page, especially going into a
challenge, there's no way we're
going to lose.
>> JEFF: What's your biggest
contribution?
>> ALICIA: I think my motivation
for everybody is probably my
biggest contribution.
I'm used to doing that back home
with my job as a personal
trainer, motivating people, and
I think it just comes naturally
to me, in any kind of situation,
to take on that motivation role.
And that's what I do, or at
least I try to.
>> JEFF: Kimmi, I've seen you in
action.
Where are you feeling in the
tribe right now, as we come to a
vote?
>> KIMMI: I don't know, just
like with anything, it could
depend on the day or the
weather, you know, what goes
through your head.
'Cause, every day, you feel
close to somebody and then you
feel a little bit separated,
and it's, um... it's weird.
>> JEFF: All right, guys.
Behind me, four torches.
Debb is the only one familiar to
you guys and another one is
going to be added to that pile
in a few minutes.
Let's do it.
Michael, you're up first.
>> KIMMI: This really should be
Alicia, but I hear other people
are voting for Jeff.
>> ALICIA: My vote is for Kimmi.
She and I have not got along
from the beginning, and the
whole food thing is really
becoming an issue that separates
her from the rest of the tribe,
so I think it's time to let her
go.
>> ELISABETH: We need to keep
our tribe strong and there's too
much split going on, so, for
a strong Kucha, it's the best
vote.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are tallied, the
decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'm going to read them.
First vote...
Kimmi.
Next vote...
That's three votes: Kimmi.
Four votes.
No need to read the rest.
Kimmi, you need to bring me your
torch.
>> KIMMI: Okay, bye, guys.
>> JEFF: The tribe and Mother
Nature have spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> KIMMI: Which way?
Go get 'em, guys.
>> JEFF: Well, the good news is:
you survived Tribal Council.
The bad news is: this is what
you get to sleep in.
Have a good long walk home.
Grab your torches, I'll see you
tomorrow.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from next time, and hear what
Kimmi has to say.
Next time on Survivor:
( man screaming )
When the unthinkable happens at
Kucha, the tribe realizes
survival in the outback is not
just a game.
>> JERRI: "There has been an
accident at the Kucha camp."
>> COLBY: Oh, my God.
>> ELISABETH: And it just really
hit hard.
>> KIMMI: I knew for a long time
that my head was on the chopping
block.
It doesn't surprise me at all.
I'm glad that I stayed true to
myself and my morals.
Um, I know that Alicia and I
have not gotten along since day
one.
If that's what they felt that
they had to do, then, you know,
power to the team.