>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Food was scarce, fishing was
tough.
>> RODGER: Tina, I got a line
hung up.
>> JEFF: And they were
dangerously low on rice.
>> JERRI: One more meal of rice
is all we have we have left?
>> TINA: At the most.
>> JEFF: Jerri wanted to team up
with Colby for the reward
challenge, but the tribe
insisted on drawing names from a
hat.
Ironically, she ended up with
Colby anyway, and they went on
to win the event, and spent a
day at the Great Barrier Reef.
>> JERRI: This is basically the
perfect honeymoon without the
sex.
>> JEFF: Nick won the immunity
challenge.
>> NICK: Yeah, baby!
>> JEFF: In a departure from
previous tribal councils, Ogakor
voted against one of their own.
>> COLBY: Jerri, Jerri, Jerri,
that knock you keep hearing on
your door-- it's checkout time.
>> JEFF: And Jerri was booted
from the tribe.
Jerri, the tribe has spoken.
Seven people left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> AMBER: Last night, at tribal
council, Jerri got voted off.
And I think that the group
definitely isolated me from
their decision because they
thought that I was too close to
Jerri.
And I felt sad, not only because
of Jerri leaving, but I think
more so because it made me feel
like my own tribe members didn't
even trust me enough to let me
know what was going on.
I felt really left out, and I
hated that feeling.
Good morning.
>> KEITH: I think Amber made a
tactical mistake by staying
tight with Jerri.
But she was visibly stunned last
night that that took place, too.
She didn't see it coming, so she
probably felt she lost her big
sister comrade last night, and
she's kind of a lone lamb out in
the midst of the rest of us now.
And she's a big girl, you know?
She made that decision early on,
and that's where she sits now.
There's nothing can be done
about it.
>> NICK: The mood will probably
be better around here.
>> AMBER: This is how much rice
we have left to last us 14 days.
This is probably enough for one
serving.
>> NICK: This is the closest to
a six-pack I've ever had.
>> COLBY: You know, we're in a
spot now, but it's not the end
of the world.
My gosh, the human body can go
days without food.
Where the lack of food comes in
is mentally.
And you've got to stay tough
mentally to make it through a
food drought like we have right
now.
And you can sit around and say,
"What if, you know, what if we
were to say...?"
Well, we don't have any rice.
Woulda, coulda, shoulda.
If ifs and buts were candy and
nuts, we'd all have a merry
Christmas.
>> TINA: And if we don't catch
our food, we won't be eating
any food.
Here on out, it's going to have
to be everybody working
together, catching crickets,
grubs, whatever we can find in
order to have people fishing,
and that's no easy task on its
own.
>> ELISABETH: You know, we're
starving.
We haven't eaten in 24 hours,
and we had a lot to do, and no
energy-- none.
Everyone here was just in slow
motion.
You know, I think everyone here
would bring back Jerri if we had
rice to come with her.
( laughing )
>> KEITH: Got him.
Look at that.
You show me Colby doing that.
A cowboy can ride bulls and
horses, but he can't catch
grasshoppers.
Oh, look at that-- it's coming
out.
>> COLBY: You know what?
I had two grasshoppers this
morning, and a frog.
But the big ones, you can't even
tire those guys out, man.
They fly forever and are very
scarce, so you can't sneak up on
those.
The ones everybody's been
fishing with is the little bitty
ones, which are pretty easy to
catch.
I haven't seen any lately.
>> KEITH: Yeah, I mean, you
expend a lot of energy catching
grasshoppers.
You chase them down, I mean,
you'll run sometimes for 100
yards... not 100 yards.
You'll run sometimes for several
yards chasing a grasshopper
down, but that grasshopper could
mean a, you know, a 15-inch
black bream, so it's very
important.
There he goes.
>> COLBY: Keith probably has the
upper hand on the whole
grasshopper wrangling.
A little more experience under
his belt.
You know, he's been at it a
while, and he kind of has a
handle on it.
>> KEITH: Just kind of stun them
a little bit.
>> COLBY: I've yet to figure out
his method, but I may have to go
to the master so he can teach
young grasshopper how to wrangle
grasshoppers.
>> KEITH: Excuse me.
I just caught a grasshopper.
Kind of important.
Oh, no.
It's like the 747 of
grasshoppers.
There you go.
I took a wing and a leg off.
I was hungry.
>> ELISABETH: Thanks.
I'm close to that.
Oh...!
A turtle.
I hate those turtles.
I'm going to try and keep calm.
I don't know whether to break
this rod or try and eat it.
E-mail.
"Elisabeth."
What is in here?
There's, like,...
>> AMBER: Money in there.
>> ELISABETH: What is this?
>> AMBER: Wait, hold on, let me
read the card.
"For this next challenge, you'll
have to be shrewd,
It's time to find out the real
value of food."
>> ELISABETH: Priceless.
"If you don't believe a snack is
worth more than gold,
Watch it going once, going
twice, and then it will be
sold."
It's going to be an auction.
>> AMBER: We all have a certain
amount of money to auction on
food.
>> ELISABETH: Check it out--
money.
>> RODGER: Wow!
>> AMBER: Yes, it's real money.
>> ELISABETH: Colby, they could
get us some peanut butter.
>> AMBER: But I think we'll all
be getting something.
>> TINA: Wow, I'm excited.
>> ELISABETH: You guys, we'll
get something.
( thunder rumbling )
>> JEFF: Okay, guys, welcome to
the Survivor auction.
You each have 500 Australian
dollars.
Up for bid-- a variety of food
items.
If you see something you desire,
bid on it.
I'll tell you what the bidding
starts at.
The increments are $20.
First item-- $60 for four tasty
Doritos and a nice big old thing
of salsa to go with it.
>> AMBER: Wow!
>> JEFF: 60 bucks; Nick?
These are the real deal, Tina.
I know how much you like
Doritos.
>> TINA: I do, but that's more
than $10 a chip.
>> JEFF: Ouch!
All right, going once, twice,
sold to Nick for 60 bucks.
Come on down.
>> TINA: Oh, my gosh!
>> AMBER: Doritos, babies!
>> NICK: 20, 40, 60.
Mmm!
>> JEFF: You can take it back
up.
Next item-- how about a
little dessert?
Big old thing of peanut butter,
four squares of chocolate.
We'll start the bidding at,
uh... oh, 80 bucks.
>> AMBER: 80 bucks.
>> ELISABETH: 100.
>> TINA: 120.
>> ELISABETH: 140.
>> JEFF: 140, Elisabeth. Amber?
That's a lot of peanut butter.
>> AMBER: 160.
>> JEFF: 180, Elisabeth.
Going once.
200, Colby.
>> ELISABETH: 220.
>> JEFF: $220 for peanut butter
and chocolate.
Going once... 240. Tina.
240.
( Tina laughing )
>> TINA: I know that that's
something that I...
>> JEFF: 260, Elisabeth, going
once, twice, sold to Elisabeth.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh, oh,
my gosh, oh, my gosh.
>> JEFF: Bring a tear to your
eye.
>> ELISABETH: I would have paid
300 for that.
This is my favorite game in the
whole world.
I'm shaking.
>> JEFF: Right on.
Go back and enjoy.
Boy, you are shaking.
>> ELISABETH: I am.
>> JEFF: Wow!
Mountain Dew.
Sold to Amber for 80 dollars.
>> AMBER: Mmm.
>> JEFF: Sold to Nick-- three
crackers for 120 dollars.
Sold to Keith for 180 dollars.
Take a bite.
Sold to Tina.
She's on the board.
Sold to Nick for 100 dollars.
Six French fries, and a big old
dish of ranch dressing to dip it
in.
Sold to Amber.
>> AMBER: Mmm!
>> JEFF: Iced coffee and
chocolate peanut butter energy
bar.
A little bit of protein.
>> AMBER: 100.
>> JEFF: Amber, 100.
120, Colby.
140, Amber.
160, Colby.
>> AMBER: 180.
>> JEFF: 180 Amber.
200 Colby.
We found something Colby wants.
>> JEFF: 240 Colby.
>> AMBER: Damn you.
>> JEFF: 260 to Amber.
280 to Colby.
Going once, twice, sold to movie
star for 280.
>> COLBY: We're eating, baby.
>> JEFF: Big-ticket item right
there.
>> COLBY: Plenty more where that
came from.
On target right there.
Thanks, Jeff.
>> JEFF: Right on.
Anybody got any money left?
>> AMBER: Yes.
Yeah, we got a lot left.
>> JEFF: Good because I've got a
nice meal here.
>> AMBER: Hold on, hold on.
Is that mashed potatoes I see
there?
>> JEFF: Mashed potatoes, bread,
turkey, a little veggie on
there.
I'm thinking this is worth a lot
at this point.
We'll start at 180.
>> AMBER: 180.
>> JEFF: 180 Amber.
200 Tina, 220 to Elisabeth.
240, Keith.
>> ELISABETH: Can I get a loan?
>> TINA: Can you sell me one
piece of your turkey and half of
your mashed potatoes?
>> ELISABETH: Yes.
>> JEFF: 260 to Elisabeth.
Keith owns it at 280.
>> ELISABETH: Will you give me
20?
>> TINA: Yeah, and I'll give you
20 more, if you want to go 300.
>> ELISABETH: I can sell her
half?
>> JEFF: 300 to Elisabeth.
>> KEITH: 320.
>> ELISABETH: That is all he
has.
>> 340.
>> JEFF: 340-- Elisabeth.
Anybody else in on that?
One, two, three, sold to
Elisabeth.
>> TINA: Yes! Go, girl!
>> JEFF: Come on down.
$340, yours.
Mystery plate.
We'll start this at 120.
>> AMBER: 120.
>> JEFF: 120, Amber.
140, Keith.
>> AMBER: 160.
>> JEFF: 160, Amber.
Thinking about it, Rodger?
180.
>> AMBER: 200.
>> JEFF: 200 to Amber.
Once, twice, three times.
200 dollars for the mystery
plate.
>> Let's see what it is.
>> AMBER: I hope it's good.
Gosh, I'll be upset.
>> JEFF: That's a tall glass of
Herbert river water.
>> KEITH: Yes!
We read that one right, didn't
we?
>> JEFF: Rodger, I think I have
something you may like.
You cannot tell me you are not
interested in a cheeseburger?
>> Oh, my God.
>> RODGER: That one's coming up
here, son.
>> JEFF: 200.
Rodger?
220.
240, Rodger?
260 Keith.
280, Rodger.
>> KEITH: Three...
>> JEFF: 300, Keith.
>> RODGER: How much money you
got?
>> JEFF: 320, Rodger.
>> RODGER: Let me at it.
Oh, go ahead, hit the gavel.
I'm ready.
>> JEFF: Once, twice, sold to
Kentucky Joe.
All good things come to those
who wait.
>> RODGER: Boy, that is good.
Thank you.
>> TINA: I'm not feeling well.
>> AMBER: I think I'm the only
one that's feeling well.
>> TINA: I can't believe it
would go through you that fast.
>> RODGER: I was feeling sick.
I thought I was going to vomit,
to tell you truth.
I guess because I haven't had
hardly any food.
And ate the cheeseburger and now
I think I'm going to have to
make a trip over the hills to
the latrine.
>> NICK: I got to use the
restroom.
>> TINA: I think that our body
is so stripped of any kind of
nutrition, you know, I had
turkey and mashed potatoes and
some bread, and it's just...
it's just going rrrr, you know,
my body's trying to process it
and it's just not going too
good.
>> AMBER: I paid $200 for river
water.
But you know what, somebody had
to do it..
>> COLBY: Here's the deal.
You paid 200 bucks for river
water and yet you and I are
standing here and everybody else
is trying to find paper bark so
they can wipe their butts,
'cause they all have to go to
the bathroom.
>> AMBER: And I feel good.
>> NICK: I'm going to go take a
bath, so the whole tent doesn't
smell like ass by the end of the
night.
>> ELISABETH: Mine wasn't that
>> NICK: Mine wasn't that bad,
but I will feel much better
when, I mean, I'm sitting here
wiping my butt with leaves.
You know, you can only get so
much with leaves, I'm sure.
>> RODGER: Boy, that felt good.
Almost as good as eating the
cheeseburger.
>> NICK: Time to get in the
river.
Makes the ass clean.
>> RODGER: That's what I was
thinking about doing.
>> ELISABETH: Our systems were
just in shock, just absolute
shock.
Hopefully that's it for me.
As good as it was, I would not
take any of that away.
I would do it all over again, I
really would.
Nothing can compare to the food.
>> RODGER: My leaf had a hole in
it, Keith.
( laughter )
( thunder crashing )
( heavy rainfall )
>> TINA: The water has risen
considerably from last night,
and we're losing ground.
And we had our flag on the other
side of our tent, and I had to
move it because we don't know
how much longer there's going to
be beach over there.
>> ELISABETH: We could have been
washed away last night?
>> TINA: We're probably going to
have to move camp today,
actually.
Today or tomorrow, no doubt.
The water's risen.
And it must be flooding upstream
because it's quickly encroaching
on us.
>> ELISABETH: It might as well
be a mine field right now, I
mean with the weather how it is.
A storm can come and just wash
our tent right out.
It's right in line with the
riverbed where it seemed to be
rushing before.
And the river's already crept
up, and consumed what we had at
camp.
I mean, we crossed that river to
get here.
It's almost doubled in size.
I mean, it's massive right now,
and it is coming for us.
>> AMBER: It just keeps on
going.
Every day, there's something
new.
Unbelievable.
I'm just in shock.
>> ELISABETH: We're in trouble.
We need to move this camp, and
my gosh, if I feel how I did
yesterday, if everyone feels how
they did yesterday, I can't even
get myself out of first gear.
You know, you go from being
starving and then going to an
auction and eating, to being
starving again.
And, you know, that one meal
isn't enough to sustain you.
It's not.
We're still depleted.
It's just... it's going to be a
rough day, and we don't have
food yet.
>> NICK: For me, not having food
is killer.
The lack of energy and the heat
and the rain, it's all real.
And tomorrow makes a month.
And a month is a long time to
lay on the ground.
I mean I'm 23 years old, in
pretty good athletic shape.
My back is killing me.
You know, I've been sick twice.
My mouth is raw.
Yesterday, I felt a lot better
after I ate, you know, I felt I
could do this for 13 more days.
But today, I'm just, like, oh,
God, please get me out of here
sometime soon.
>> ELISABETH: Good call, coach.
>> RODGER: Ooh, he liked the
hook, too, didn't he?
That's had a nice one.
Look how fat he is.
Oh, man.
>> TINA: Rodger's been out
fishing.
Elisabeth's been out fishing.
I've been out fishing.
Has Nick been out fishing?
No.
He was asked to go fishing, but
he said that he's never been
before and he wasn't planning on
starting now.
>> ELISABETH: Why, you know, let
your friends work extra hard
because you don't want to get up
and move, because you don't feel
like moving?
We're all sick here.
I mean, we're all weak, and I
never thought I'd say this.
I really never thought I would,
but I'm really disappointed in
Nick right now.
I really am.
You know, maybe we're the dumb
ones.
Maybe he's smart, saving his
energy and sleeping all day to
win immunity.
If we're... Rodger and I are out
there, you know, blowing all of
our energy on fishing and Nick
is conserving his energy wisely,
he's going to keep winning
immunity challenges, and that's
going to leave with a vote to
one of us, you know, either
Rodger or myself.
And that's scary.
That makes me mad.
>> NICK: I feel vulnerable
because I still remain a
physical threat to win
challenges.
I won the last immunity
challenge.
I'm a big body, so I take a lot
to feed.
So I'm feeling vulnerable.
If I don't win the immunity
challenge, I definitely expect
to go.
>> JEFF: I need to take the
immunity necklace back.
>> NICK: There you go.
>> JEFF: Immunity back up for
grabs.
All right, the ability to start
fire quickly, essential to
survival in the outback.
Whether it's just to signal a
passing plane or to create
warmth, fire skills got to be
sharp.
For today's challenge, you'll
each be assigned a fire scale.
On one end, a fire bucket.
On the other end, a water
bucket.
Your goal: create fire in that
fire bucket and then by putting
water in the water bucket, tilt
the scale to raise the fire high
enough to light a fuse at the
top.
The first person to light the
fuse wins immunity.
Here's the hiccup.
Your water bucket has a hole in
it, so it's going to be a
constant battle running to the
river to gather water...
>> TINA: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: ...and making sure your
fire still has flame.
Sound good?
>> TINA: It sounds good.
>> JEFF: They're all the same.
Pick one and let's go.
>> AMBER: So there's always a
catch.
It's so funny.
>> JEFF: Everybody knows where
their matches are, right?
>> RODGER: Yeah.
>> JEFF: For immunity, survivors
ready?
Go!
Two people going for water
already.
That-a-way, Rodger.
Keep cooking, Keith.
Don't be deceived.
You're making progress.
Right now, we've got a lot of
fires burning.
Ladies and gents, get moving.
Hey, hey, hey.
No, no.
>> KEITH: Just checking balance.
>> JEFF: Don't check.
I know you guys are getting
tired.
The good news is your fires are
doing great.
>> NICK: Not mine.
>> JEFF: Except for you, Nick.
>> NICK: Too late to stop now.
>> KEITH: Oh, come on, come on,
come on.
>> JEFF: You're getting there,
Keith.
>> ELISABETH: There's a hole in
the bucket, dear Liza.
>> KEITH: Swing on the pot.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, baby.
Yeah! No.
Stay there.
No.
>> JEFF: You're close
Don't slow down.
>> COLBY: Yeah! Whoa! Yeah!
>> JEFF: Right here, man.
Nice work, out of nowhere.
>> COLBY: Come from behind.
>> RODGER: I've got to have
something to eat around here.
It makes everybody scared if we
don't have a little something.
>> TINA: Nutritionally, our body
is going into shock.
None of us are used to being
this weak and not knowing really
what to do about it.
I know Elisabeth is not doing
well at all.
She had a very hard time getting
up this morning, just making it
out of the tent this morning,
I'm really concerned about her.
>> NICK: Let's take a load off
and get some water.
>> ELISABETH: I'm just going to
drink some water.
I'm feeling terrible.
I mean, but I'm just, like,
shaking and weak, and I'm just
frustrated with how I feel.
I couldn't even walk up the hill
to fish.
I mean, I hate not being able to
help out and get some food.
We need to get rice today.
I just want my strength back.
I'm just nauseous and, like,...
oh, man.
>> NICK: It's hard to get
started in the morning.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah.
We have nothing to sustain us
through the morning today.
We're praying for fish.
We have only two hooks right
now.
>> TINA: No luck.
Not even any bites.
Rodger got a turtle.
>> RODGER: He pulled the hook
off, so there goes another hook.
>> ELISABETH: I'm sorry I
couldn't make it out here
sooner.
I just had a rough morning.
>> RODGER: Why don't you come
back and rest, and then we're
going to go back out in a couple
of hours.
>> ELISABETH: Okay.
>> RODGER: Only bite I had was
that stupid turtle.
>> ELISABETH: I'm just real low.
>> RODGER: Yeah, Jeff's here.
He's got a big thing of rice.
>> TINA: He has a bad look on
his face.
>> JEFF: What's up, guys?
>> RODGER: Is that ours?
>> JEFF: I come today because
I'm concerned, because yesterday
at the immunity challenge, I saw
something that I haven't seen
before-- true lethargy, a real
lack of energy, especially with
Elisabeth and Nick.
You've got 13 days left.
And I don't think you're going
to make it.
So it puts me in an awkward
situation, because you had
plenty of stuff.
If rationed properly, you had
enough rice and you had 25
hooks.
You had a tackle box you
couldn't improve on.
So what happened with the rice?
I mean why are you out?
>> COLBY: We just weren't
careful with our rations.
There's not any one person to
blame.
We're all guilty.
>> TINA: We did each lose a bag,
too, to condensation in the can.
>> COLBY: But that's our own
fault.
>> TINA: I'm not saying it's not
our fault.
But you just asked what
happened, and that's part of
what happened.
>> JEFF: Here's where we're at.
My role is a giver and a taker.
Nothing comes cheap.
I have enough rice to last you
your last two weeks here.
>> AMBER: There's so much rice
there.
>> JEFF: But it's not coming
without a price, so I need
something back.
And I need something of value,
substantial value to get this
rice.
>> RODGER: Blankets.
I think blankets would be a good
tradeoff.
>> JEFF: Rodger, I'm talking
serious value.
You guys are playing for...
>> RODGER: You're laying there
shivering some night, those
blankets are of serious value.
>> JEFF: We're playing for $1
million.
>> TINA: Of what we have, what
do you want?
>> JEFF: I'm talking camp.
>> TINA: Camp? Our tent?
>> JEFF: Shelter versus food,
it's one or the other.
Your tarps and that Texas flag.
That's what I want.
>> AMBER: You want all the tarps
and the flag?
>> ELISABETH: All the tarps?
>> RODGER: How are we going to
keep dry when it rains?
It rains every day.
>> TINA: We could use rain
jackets, the top and the sleeve.
>> COLBY: I mean, shelter,
though.
That's a no-brainer.
I'm talking about my personal
item here.
I have no problem giving it up.
>> JEFF: Let me entice you a
little more:
25 more hooks.
>> TINA: Oh, absolutely.
You can have the shelter, as far
as... my vote is take the
shelter.
>> ELISABETH: And if we have
energy, we can build something.
>> JEFF: Let's do it.
>> TINA: Thank you, Jeff.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: Who's got the strength
to tear it down?
I hate to have you disrupt
everything, but...
>> AMBER: We need our food, and
we need to your strength.
>> JEFF: Got to have a value.
Your tarps and that big old
Texas flag, engineered to be a
tarp.
>> COLBY: Take care of that,
please.
>> JEFF: I will.
Good negotiation, guys.
>> COLBY: Thank you very much.
>> JEFF: I hope the food gives
you the strength to rebuild...
>> ELISABETH: It will.
>> JEFF: ...to get through the
last two weeks.
>> AMBER: Thank you.
>> JEFF: Thanks, Rodger.
All right, I'll see you guys
tonight...
>> KEITH: All right, Jeff.
>> JEFF: ...when we have the
unfortunate business of dealing
with the tribal council.
So, eat up today.
Bye, guys.
>> COLBY: Once we realized that,
oh, my God, our shelter's gone,
the first thing we seemed to
have to do was get a roof over
our head 'cause it really seemed
like it was going to rain pretty
hard today.
>> RODGER: It's going to be
pouring down rain here tonight.
>> TINA: We need to start
looking for a tree cover.
>> COLBY: Actually, up in this
thing would probably be the best
just because there are so many
places to lay branches in here.
>> TINA: The only downside is if
the river comes up again.
I don't think we need to bring
the woods to us; I think we need
to go to the woods.
>> ELISABETH: Mm-hmm.
>> KEITH: So then it was trying
to decide where the shelter was
going to be.
And we had a little food this
morning but not enough to climb
with a hill and build a shelter
up in the hills, that's for
sure.
>> RODGER: We want to come in
here with some limbs and angle
them down so it will run as much
water off as we can.
>> TINA: I think it was a fair
trade.
If we can keep the rains away,
as long as it's not a torrential
downpour.
We may get wet.
But there's worse things in life
than being wet, such as starving
to death.
>> COLBY: Hey, Nick, can you
bring some of that brush down?
>> TINA: Think chopping up this
chest is good?
We're using everything that we
possibly can at this point.
Every little bit helps.
>> RODGER: I got some more.
>> NICK: All right.
>> TINA: What do you need most
of right now?
We got grass.
>> COLBY: I need grass and pine,
that's it.
It's looking solid already.
>> TINA: Maybe it won't even
rain tonight.
>> COLBY: Maybe not.
( thunder rumbling )
>> TINA: Maybe so.
>> NICK: Maybe so.
>> AMBER: I feel a couple of
raindrops.
>> TINA: Might as well get used
to it.
>> NICK: These branches are not
going to keep us totally dry.
It's going to be more water-
resistant than waterproof.
>> RODGER: At least we got food,
brother.
>> COLBY: Amber's a little bit
nervous about the fact that we
voted Jerri off.
She felt like she might be the
next one that we go after.
That way Amber won't know
anything.
>> KEITH: A smart move.
>> COLBY: It could be
potentially deadly for all three
of us.
>> AMBER: Can you help me carry
this?
>> COLBY: She and Elisabeth have
been bonding quite well.
She could very easily go over
to the guys from Kucha and say,
"Hey, look, I know they're going
after me next.
I want to jump on with you
guys."
>> ELISABETH: If I were Amber,
I'd feel threatened.
I mean, if everyone can make
Jerri go away, she can just as
easily go away.
But by voting Jerri off, Ogakor
diluted their power a bit.
It didn't seem to be the
smartest strategic thing to do.
>> AMBER: Okay, guys.
>> ELISABETH: And, now, I think
they are worried about Amber
approaching us.
Amber is kind of a pivot in the
whole Barramundi scenario.
Bon appétit.
>> TINA: That is good rice.
It's so nice to have rice again.
>> AMBER: I could approach the
Kucha people and go against
Colby, Tina and Keith.
And it would be four against
three and we could just pick
them off one by one.
But how do I know that I can
100% trust the Kucha members,
that they're not just playing
with my mind and just pretending
to agree with me?
I guess I don't know if I can
trust Ogakor people, too.
They could be playing with my
mind, too, but I have to play
the game.
And the game's getting harder
and harder as the days go on.
>> RODGER: We need to be heading
out.
I guess we're ready.
>> AMBER: Let's go.
>> RODGER: You're not bringing
anything, Keith?
>> JEFF: We'll now bring in our
jury: Alicia and Jerri.
I'll remind you that the jury's
not to be addressed.
They won't address you.
They're merely here to gather
information to help them
determine who's going to get the
$1 million and the title of
Survivor.
Okay, first things first.
What was the reaction after I
left, with all your tarps and
your Texas flag that you guys
have food?
Tina, did you feel the
negotiation was fair?
>> TINA: I definitely feel like
it was fair.
That was something that we could
rebuild.
And even though you took it away
from us, it's not like it
couldn't be replaced.
And so, to be quite honest, I
was grateful that that's what
you chose.
>> JEFF: Nick, obviously, you
came into this a very fit guy.
Are you surprised at the toll
it's taken on your body?
>> NICK: I'm definitely
surprised.
I mean, I stood up today and I
felt like I was really going to
pass out.
I was waving back and forth and
felt bad.
And the last three days have
been so incredibly tough.
>> JEFF: Direct question: Colby,
anybody here not pulling their
weight?
>> COLBY: No.
I don't think so.
>> JEFF: Rodger?
>> RODGER: Overall, I think
it's... everybody's been pulling
their weight.
>> JEFF: Amber, how have you
grown as a person, being out
here 28 days now?
>> AMBER: I am a lot more open
than I ever thought I would be,
and I'm willing to try new
things and do new things.
And I'm a much riskier person
now.
It might have taken a really
hard experience to learn that
about myself, but I think it's
definitely worth it.
>> JEFF: I want you guys to just
take a second and look at Alicia
and Jerri.
Slowly the power base shifts
from this side to that side.
In the end, it comes down to
politics.
How can you possibly vote
somebody out and get their vote
at the end?
I just want to remind you of
that as we go vote.
Elisabeth, you're up.
>> NICK: My vote is for Keith
tonight because, unlike
everybody else, he didn't feel
the need to bring his backpack,
and that's just flat out
arrogance.
>> TINA: You seem like a really
great guy, but you said you were
tired of playing the game, and
that you weren't having fun
anymore.
So, here's your ticket, buddy.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
I'll read the votes.
The first vote, Nick.
Amber.
Keith.
Two votes, Amber.
Nick.
Two votes, Nick.
Two votes, Amber.
One vote, Keith.
That's three votes, Nick.
Last vote...
Nick.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> NICK: You guys play tough.
>> RODGER: See you later.
>> ELISABETH: Bye.
>> RODGER: Hang in there.
Hang in there.
>> NICK: I hope it doesn't rain
tonight.
>> JEFF: Nick, the tribe has
spoken.
>> TINA: Bye, Nick.
>> JEFF: For the rest of you
guys, I wish for you dry, hot
weather with no rain.
You can head back to camp.
I'll see you tomorrow.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode, and hear
what Nick has to say.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
>> ELISABETH: This game, in the
past three days, has become
drastically primal.
>> JEFF: Has Barramundi been
pushed to the brink, or is their
greatest challenge yet to come?
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
>> RODGER: Our camp is a dry
creek bed.
I doubt if it's dry right now.
>> NICK: It's been a great
adventure, have some great
times, and some big blows.
The last few days have
been really rough on me, and
it's taught me a lot about not
only my strengths but more
importantly my weaknesses.
I kind of feel invincible at
times, and Survivor has been a
big reality check for me.
It's been a ride, it's
definitely been a ride.