>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Kucha and Ogakor merged into one
tribe at equal numbers with five
members each, calling
themselves Barramundi.
The tribe set up camp on a new
beach and started from scratch.
( cheering )
In a test of endurance, the
first individual immunity
challenge lasted over ten hours.
Tina stepped down to give the
more vulnerable Keith immunity,
so that the ex-Ogakor tribe
could take the advantage at
Tribal Council.
So, we're ruling this a deadlock
vote.
Colby and Jeff were deadlocked
into tie, so Jeff's votes at
previously Tribal Councils
tipped the scales, and Jeff was
voted out of the tribe.
Nine survivors remain.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> RODGER: It's a late-sleeping
bunch, isn't it?
>> ALICIA: Yeah.
>> RODGER: A lot different
than... than us.
>> ALICIA: I know.
>> RODGER: Mike would've been up
three hours ago.
>> ALICIA: I know.
>> RODGER: Every time I do that,
I think about old Mike.
>> ALICIA: No kidding.
>> RODGER: And, you know, every
time from now on, when we're...
when we're around the fire, we
will think of it.
>> ALICIA: Yep.
>> RODGER: After the last Tribal
Council, I just felt like we had
been outwitted by Ogakor.
Kucha's tribe could be picked
off very easily.
They're in a good position to do
that.
We could be an extinct tribe, no
longer on the face of the earth.
To me, it's, uh, one-on-one and
every man for himself from here
on out.
See, I can catch 'em.
I am in it to win just like
anybody else.
I'm going to give it my best
shot.
My game plan right now to try to
assure my survival is try to
keep catching fish.
Ooh, yes.
If they're going to vote
somebody off, it's going to
probably not be the person that
is supplying 'em with the food.
I think that is my greatest
asset at this time.
I love this fishing hole. Whoo!
>> NICK: Wow, look at that
crocodile.
Do not want to go in that water
again.
>> ALICIA: This game has
definitely changed.
There's no doubt about it.
It's a whole new game.
New people. New set of rules.
>> NICK: You keep on catching
fish, you'll definitely be the
last of Kutcha to go.
( laughing )
>> ALICIA: Ogakor knows they're
in a good position now to be the
last five, but they also have to
know that four members on this
jury now are going to be Kucha
members, and these people decide
who's going to be the winner.
They better start stepping up
and being real nice to us.
>> KEITH: I feel like I'm on a
fishing trip with you.
It's like I'm with... you're my
older brother and taking me
fishing.
>> RODGER: Everybody is-is real
nice to everybody else, but then
you can still see groups getting
off and talking, and you know
what they're talking about.
You know the million dollars for
being the final survivor is on
everybody's mind.
>> AMBER: We're exactly where we
want to be.
>> COLBY: As a team, Ogakor, we
outplayed 'em.
>> AMBER: It's just, like, I
feel, like, some pressure has
been lifted off my shoulders.
>> COLBY: I agree.
I... I'm sleeping so much better
now after getting past the merge
and the final... the final vote
to see who-who grabs the
majority.
>> AMBER: I know.
>> COLBY: And we won.
>> AMBER: Geez!
>> KEITH: Yeah, I think Ogakor
was definitely a team that
stayed out of vision knowing
that we needed to whittle down
the Kucha people.
Kucha knows what we're doing.
They are really good, nice
people, which does make it
harder as the days go on.
And the closer you become to an
individual, you start
questioning, "Geez, you know, I
like this person better than
somebody I know on my own team."
>> RODGER: Well, if I had to
guess, I'd say somebody in your
all's group is going to be a
millionaire.
>> KEITH: Well, you know, help
yourself out, my friend.
It just seems natural that
certain individuals gravitate to
each other, and Tina and I have
made the decision that we want
to be with people we like right
at the very end.
>> ELISABETH: You know Rodger
has my heart. I love him.
>> TINA: He's a good one.
>> ELISABETH: I love him.
See, I knew you guys would hit
it off, too.
>> TINA: I like him.
You go into a merger thinking
that you're very much aligned
with a team, but then, as time
goes by, you might find out that
there's people that are more
deserving, you know?
I want this to be on an
individual basis, and I want the
good guys to win.
>> JERRI: Today has been just
so... weird.
I feel, like, a lot of distance
between myself and everybody
else right now.
We do have the advantage now.
We're five... Kucha's...
to Kucha's four, but that's not
relaxing me at all.
It's the paranoia again setting
in.
We're in a situation where Tina
and Keith could team up with the
Kucha people.
You cannot be complacent.
Your back will be stabbed faster
than you can spit.
( clattering )
Ooh!
>> TINA: Ever since the
beginning, the cooking of the
rice has been a problem.
It was a problem at Ogakor, and
the same problem came with us to
Barramundi.
Basically, what it is is the
rice has to be cooked to Jerri's
specifications.
It has to be stirred a certain
number of times.
The lid has to stay on.
It has to be... perfect, you
know, or... you-you catch it.
>> What kind of spices we
have tonight, ladies?
>> ELISABETH: A little parmesan
pizza mix.
>> ALICIA: The lemon pepper is
not great on the rice.
>> AMBER: It's not?
>> ALICIA: No.
Not great.
>> ELISABETH: Alicia and I were
on the side of the fire, and
Jerri and Amber were sitting on
a log just watching every move
we made.
Every time I would... I would
take a lid off, I could see
them, you know, tensing up,
like, you know, "Why is she
taking the lid off?
Why is she stirring now?"
>> AMBER: Be careful.
>> TINA: They're not going to
go.
They're not going to go.
>> AMBER: If you guys have a
knife, a knife might be easier
to stir.
>> ELISABETH: Well, don't even
worry about it.
>> TINA: She actually got it.
>> AMBER: You got it?
>> ELISABETH: Alicia and I were
getting more tense trying to
make it.
You know, we were testing the
rice.
We always test to it make sure
it's done, and Jerri's over on
her log.
"It's mushy," she says.
>> JERRI: Mashed potatoes.
>> ELISABETH: I know you don't
like mushy... but it's mushy.
>> ALICIA: I'll stir it until
it's done.
>> JERRI: I guess it doesn't
really matter.
It's such crappy rice, anyway.
>> ELISABETH: I felt as if I
were under a magnifying glass,
and I do not need to be meant to
feel that way at all.
Like, don't tell me what I'm
supposed to be doing when I'm
making you dinner. Don't.
>> TINA: Whenever you have a
whole bunch, it's really hard to
make it, I think.
Poor little old Elisabeth was
sitting there trying to cook the
rice, and Jerri made some
comments about it.
It hurt Elisabeth's feelings,
because here she is, trying to
help the tribe, and then to not
be appreciated for it and to be
judged-- that's very hurtful.
And I think that right there
probably was enough for
Elisabeth to say, "You know
what?
You'll get my vote."
I try to stay away from cooking,
so I don't have to be judged.
>> JERRI: Ah!
>> ELISABETH: Within Ogakor, I
already am spotting some cracks.
There is definite dissent
between Tina and Jerri.
Does everybody have something to
eat with?
>> TINA: Yes.
>> ALICIA: Okay, hold on.
>> COLBY: Amber? Thank you.
>> Rodger would like to say a
blessing.
>> TINA: That's a good idea.
>> You ready?
>> RODGER: Yes, everybody ready?
>> Okay.
>> RODGER: Father God, we give
Thee thanks today for this
beautiful Lord's day and for all
Thy many wonderful blessings.
We thank Thee, dear Lord, for
this opportunity which we have
as a group to come to know one
another.
>> ELISABETH: If things are
going to get really crazy,
especially now, you know, and
seeing that there is a hole in
Ogakor, it kind of opens the
door to really take advantage of
that.
If they're not all together,
their plan's kind of wrecked.
>> RODGER: All these things we
ask in the name of our lord and
savior, Jesus Christ. Amen.
>> ALL: Amen.
>> TINA: Thank you, Rodger.
>> JERRI: That was nice.
>> ELISABETH: It wasn't until
today that I really started
feeling like, "Okay, Elisabeth,
do what you can do to take Kucha
to a victory.
"If you want to keep playing
this game... you better get a
little more ruthless."
>> RODGER: I'm going to try to
catch something with a cork and
I just bet I don't have any
luck.
>> ALICIA: With a cork?
>> RODGER: Yeah.
Oh, we're just sitting ducks
now.
>> ALICIA: You know what?
>> RODGER: Sitting ducks sitting
by the fire.
>> ALICIA: Whatever.
It's not fun anymore.
Laying down and talking to
everybody at night is not as
much fun as it used to be.
>> RODGER: No, no, no...
>> ALICIA: You know?
Waking up in the morning and
seeing everybody's face-- not as
fun as it used to be.
It's not fun anymore.
>> ELISABETH: You're not here to
sit back and wait for someone to
vote you off.
I just really would love to just
light a fire under everyone.
Well, that makes me sick.
I'm not going to sit here and be
a sitting duck.
No one else wants to keep
playing, I'll do whatever it
takes to stay out here longest
and keep, keep Kucha going.
I think there's a crack in their
tribe right now. Watch.
You guys, pay attention to Jerri
and Tina.
Pay real...
>> RODGER: You think it's going
to be women against the men?
>> ELISABETH: Pay attention
to...
>> ALICIA: No.
>> ELISABETH: No, because I
think Jerri and Tina have
issues.
>> ALICIA: And, well, Jerri and
Keith...
>> ELISABETH: Watch out, 'cause
she might be fishing around
here.
>> ALICIA: Jerri and Keith
definitely do.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah.
>> RODGER: I'd like to see...
>> ALICIA: Jerri does not love
Keith.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah. You guys,
honestly, well, I mean, I know
Jerri would be my next vote.
>> ALICIA: Right.
>> ELISABETH: Jerri, I think...
I think she's gonna get votes
from their tribe.
I honestly do.
>> ALICIA: I'll tell you what.
She definitely has the hots for
Colby, and he is not at all...
He just could care less.
>> ELISABETH: I'm hoping Kucha
will have some pull, 'cause
people can't stand Jerri anyway
in her own tribe, and I told
them that maybe we could
approach Keith and Tina and say,
"Look, we'd like to get rid of
Jerri.
We're going to vote for Jerri,
too," grab some of their people
and have them come with us.
>> RODGER: It's gonna be fun
these last few days whatever
happens.
>> Say something.
>> ALICIA: I'm planning on
having fun.
>> RODGER: Yeah.
>> ALICIA: I really don't care
anymore.
I'm going to go all out.
Elisabeth, although she comes
across as a, you know, a very
meek and mild kind of person,
she is a serious competitor.
Believe me, Elisabeth is a force
to be reckoned with.
See, look at them.
>> TINA: Nick's cooking two
fish.
>> ELISABETH: I know.
Tina and I have become close.
I mean close, outback close.
Outback close is close enough to
get the dirt you want on someone
else.
Close enough to let you advance
ahead of the person you're
trying to get close to.
But then, last night, she's,
like, complaining about how
we're doing the rice.
I don't know how you dealt with
her that long in your tribe.
>> TINA: Not an easy thing,
sister.
She'll get hers. It's coming.
>> ELISABETH: Ogakor's target is
Jerri.
I mean, the talk I just had with
Tina-- she can't take Jerri.
Neither can Keith, and they are
trying to get votes for her.
I don't know if I'm just a dumb
optimist or just in denial, but
I think Jerri is ready to go.
I'll say it for her, "Jerri,
you're ready to go."
>> RODGER: We got mail.
>> TINA: Oh, my goodness!
( gasps )
Colorful mail.
>> RODGER: Boomerangs?
>> TINA: Oh, my gosh.
Look at that.
>> RODGER: Oh, we're gonna have
a boomerang contest.
>> TINA: Mail, guys.
>> RODGER: And boomerangs.
So, what do think?
>> TINA: "The next challenge is
easy.
Just catch the return, and a
good start for the morning, the
winner will earn."
>> RODGER: You got to throw it
and catch it.
You got to throw it and catch
it.
>> Oh.
>> I've never thrown a
boomerang.
>> RODGER: Without getting...
Without getting hooked in the
teeth with it.
>> AMBER: Are we going to have
to, like, throw it at something
and like...?
>> NICK: No. You got to make it
come around in a circle and then
catch it.
>> ALICIA: You got to make it
come back and catch it.
( chortling )
♪ ♪
>> JEFF: Okay, guys.
Today's reward challenge,
boomerang toss.
Most popular weapon in
Australia.
It's pretty simple.
You stand inside the white
circle and throw the boomerang.
The person whose boomerang comes
closest to the red flag wins the
reward.
Make sense?
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> ALL: Yes!
>> JEFF: All right, Jerri, come
here.
( Jerri laughs )
>> JEFF: I'll let you read this
off to the, uh...
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: ...to the troops.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, it's a menu!
>> JERRI: "Appetizer..."
>> AMBER: Oh.
( Jerri laughs )
>> JERRI: "Smoked salmon and
shrimp.
Entree: grilled chicken, pasta
medley, Greek salad, rolls with
butter."
>> AMBER: Oh! Rolls...
>> JERRI: "Delicious
desserts, du jour."
It's a full meal!
>> Oh!
>> JERRI: And it's a nice one.
>> AMBER: Rolls.
>> ELISABETH: Rounds?
Like, not just one.
>> JEFF: All right, let's go.
♪ ♪
>> JEFF: Alicia!
>> ALICIA: Yeah, yo.
>> JEFF: Take your shot.
>> Go, Alicia!
>> Alicia!
( applause and cheering )
>> RODGER: Go!
>> JEFF: Pick one weapon.
>> ALICIA: Just one?
>> JEFF: Just one.
All right, get up there, girl.
>> ALICIA: All right.
>> JEFF: Give her a good run.
♪ ♪
>> It's coming back.
>> JEFF: Mark to beat, right
here, Alicia.
Next thrower.
>> KEITH: Come on, baby, come
on, baby, come back to papa!
Come on back to papa.
>> JEFF: Alicia still the mark
to beat.
>> ALICIA: No.
>> ALICIA: It may be.
>> No.
>> JEFF: It's open.
One decent toss, one good meal.
Look at that.
>> ALICIA: That's a good one!
>> Jerri!
>> ALL: Yeah!
( applause and cheering )
>> JEFF: Nicely done.
>> TINA: Good job!
>> All right.
( indistinct chatter )
>> JEFF: It's gonna be tough to
beat.
Jerri, right here.
>> ELISABETH: You've been
hungry...
>> TINA: ...for the rest of this
trip, if you get supper tonight.
>> JERRI: Oh, never.
>> TINA: Okay?
>> JERRI: If I get... supper!
>> JEFF: South paw time.
Big mark to beat.
>> NICK: Jerri's getting hungry.
>> JERRI: Ooh, that was good.
>> JERRI & TINA: Whoa!
>> All right.
>> JEFF: Jerri is still in the
lead.
>> JERRI: I'm so scared.
>> JEFF: Give it a go, Rodger.
>> Oh.
>> JERRI: Oh!
>> JEFF: Nope.
Close.
>> RODGER: Close, but no...
no supper.
>> JEFF: Jerri has the throw to
beat.
>> AMBER: Up, next person.
>> JERRI: Good luck, Amber.
>> ALICIA: All right, Amber.
>> Whoo!
>> JERRI: You're it, right?
>> AMBER: Yup.
>> ALICIA: It's you or Jerri.
>> JEFF: One challenger left.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God!
>> Oh.
>> JEFF: We better measure that.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> ALICIA: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: About an inch past
11...
>> JERRI: I am sweating.
>> TINA: Don't even look.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: Yup.
Close, but no cigar.
>> AMBER: Jerri is the winner.
>> ELISABETH: You got it.
You have it.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> AMBER: You beat me, like, a
few inches.
>> ELISABETH: Hungry girl, go
now.
>> JEFF: How ironic that you
were the one who read the menu.
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> ALICIA: Yup.
>> JEFF: Yeah.
>> JERRI: That is kind of
bizarre.
>> Way to go, Jerri.
>> JEFF: Anything on there
interest you in particular?
>> JERRI: Every last thing on
there.
>> JEFF: Yeah?
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> JEFF: All right.
Let's go eat.
>> JERRI: Right now?
>> JEFF: Yeah.
>> Oh, have...
>> Bye.
>> JERRI: This is bittersweet,
though, really.
( all talking at once )
>> COLBY: Please, come on.
>> JERRI: No, I'm serious.
>> COLBY: We're going back to
rice.
What do you mean?
Come on.
>> JERRI: I know, everybody's
hungry.
>> RODGER: ...Your help with the
rice tonight.
>> JERRI: Okay, good.
Good.
( indistinct chatter )
>> JEFF: You know, there is
enough food for one more.
Yeah, you should pick somebody
else to come.
>> JERRI: Who really, really,
really, really wants this?
>> AMBER: We all do.
>> We all...
>> You already won it. Just...
>> JEFF: Jerri, I think...
Yeah, I think it's on you.
>> Jerri, just pick.
>> Just pick...
>> JERRI: Yeah.
Amber.
>> AMBER: You picked me?
>> JERRI: You-You got...
You got the closest to me, and
you scared my pants.
>> AMBER: Thank you.
>> Bye, guys.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
I feel like I just won the Miss
America pageant.
>> AMBER: I know.
( laughter )
>> JEFF: All right, let's head
right over here.
Wait until you guys see the
setup.
>> JERRI: Oh!
>> JEFF: Jerri, you can have a
seat over here.
Amber...
Have her slide in here.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
Look at the rolls!
Oh, my God.
>> JERRI: You were just talking
about rolls today.
>> AMBER: I love rolls!
>> JERRI: Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
Can this really be real?
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: Cheers to you guys.
Begin.
>> JERRI: Cheers!
>> AMBER: Cheers.
Thank you for choosing me.
>> JERRI: Thank you!
>> AMBER: Oh, my God, is that so
good!
>> JERRI: Iced tea.
>> AMBER: Let's take our first
bite.
>> JERRI: Oh, my gosh, I'm
eating a shrimp.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
>> JERRI: I don't even care that
my fingernails are completely
and totally dirty.
>> AMBER: There you go.
( Jerri laughs )
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
>> JERRI: Mmm.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
>> AMBER: I'm gonna try the
salmon.
>> JEFF: So what's going on back
at camp?
>> JERRI: They're making rice
over there, but they've got two
extra helpings of rice, so...
( laughs )
>> JEFF: Great trade off.
>> AMBER: Right, right.
( Amber laughs )
Yeah.
Things are going good, though,
as far as, like, people getting
along and everything.
>> ELISABETH: This is the first
time since we got here that I
feel just, like, kind of just
relaxed, hanging out.
>> KEITH: Isn't it nice?
>> ELISABETH: Enjoying dinner.
Yeah.
>> ALICIA: This is how it...
>> KEITH: What's missing?
What's making it feel that way?
What could that be?
How can I put my finger on that?
( someone gasps )
>> ...spaghetti.
>> ALICIA: You know what's kind
of weird?
>> KEITH: The Wicked Witch of
the West isn't here.
>> ALICIA: How could Amber have
acted so...
>> KEITH: That's what it is.
>> ALICIA: ...surprised that she
was the beauty queen...
>> KEITH: It's all fake.
>> ALICIA: ...that knew she was
going to win...
>> KEITH: It's all fake.
Yeah, exactly.
>> ALICIA: And-And, like, was,
like, "Oh, my god!"
>> KEITH: Did you see...?
>> ALICIA: Did you see her face?
I looked at her, like, "Okay,
Amber."
>> KEITH: You chose me?!
>> ELISABETH: It was kind of
funny, because everyone else
kind of felt like we won the
reward.
That was probably the one time I
felt like Barramundi.
We just kind of hung out.
Everyone kind of vented about
how they feel about Jerri, and
it was an eye-opener to some
people.
I knew it.
>> KEITH: Well, see, I cooked
for two Presidents, I've cooked
for all kinds of people...
>> ELISABETH: Have you really?
>> KEITH: And I've never, ever,
ever been stressed.
Other than these last so many
days.
>> Isn't that weird?!
>> KEITH: Never been stressed.
>> I can't believe that.
>> KEITH: Over cooking rice!
>> ALICIA: Over rice.
>> Beautiful.
>> TINA: I'm so excited.
I love spaghetti.
I'm so excited.
>> ELISABETH: This isn't gonna
make a difference to me.
I'll have rice.
Honestly, please, because...
I'm not kidding.
>> TINA: Thank you, Elisabeth.
>> ELISABETH: One of my worst
foods.
>> TINA: You are so sweet.
Thank you.
Thank you for, like, Elisabeth,
giving some of her spaghetti!
( laughs )
>> ELISABETH: I just haven't
seen you enjoy anything like
this, Tina, like no reward...
>> AMBER: Talk about Tina being
extra chipper...
She's had a constant smile on
her face since the merge.
>> JERRI: Mm-hmm.
>> AMBER: She's been talking in
a different voice.
>> JERRI: I know.
>> AMBER: "Oh, you want to go do
this?
Want to go do that?"
( speaking gibberish )
It's unbelievable.
She's a completely different
person.
>> JERRI: You got to really keep
your eye on Tina, 'cause she has
been acting really weird.
I'm, like, so sure that she's
going to back stab us.
>> AMBER: Oh, I totally agree.
>> JERRI: Well... and she'd be
doing it with people who would
be ready to jump ship.
>> AMBER: Yeah.
>> JERRI: Jump right on her
ship.
>> AMBER: Mm-hmm. It's a
completely different game.
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> AMBER: Isn't it weird?
Playing for yourself is
definitely different.
>> JERRI: So, we need to talk to
Colby.
>> AMBER: Yeah.
>> JERRI: To making it to the
end.
>> AMBER: Yeah.
>> ELISABAETH: I just would
never want to have to make that
decision.
>> COLBY: Hey, ladies.
>> JERRI: Hi, you guys!
>> AMBER: Hi. We come bearing
gifts.
>> JERRI: You guys, we got
boomerangs.
There's one bent one and one
straight one for everybody.
>> AMBER: Everybody gets two.
It was very weird coming back to
the tribe after we had eaten our
meal.
Like, nobody even turned around
to look at us.
It was very uncomfortable.
I didn't like the feeling at
all.
>> TINA: What kind of dessert
did you get?
>> AMBER: I don't want to say
anything.
>> JERRI: I know. We-we feel...
guilty.
>> TINA: She doesn't want to
hear it.
We had a great time.
Don't you feel bad at all.
>> COLBY: When Jerri and Amber
came back, I made my way down to
the beach just to get some...
grab some time alone, and Jerri
came up, sat down beside me and
decided it was time for us to
talk.
>> JERRI: The next person Amber
and my concern... with Tina and
Keith taking off and gathering
three Kuchas...
>> COLBY: Mm-hmm.
>> JERRI: And coming after us.
She said the same as me-- like,
she wouldn't doubt it, after
that whole episode with Tina
before.
It's not good for us to just
assume that we can trust her.
Colby's kind of middle ground.
Nobody really knows what he's...
what he's going to do, and he's
not really letting anyone onto
what his plans are.
I mean, have you ever considered
maybe... maybe, um... even
leading Keith and Tina to
believe that you want the three
of them to be the final three?
>> COLBY: Keith and Tina?
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> COLBY: And myself?
>> JERRI: Have you... have you
ever thought maybe...?
>> COLBY: Oh, they're fully
convinced that's what's going to
happen.
>> JERRI: Oh, they are?
>> COLBY: I mean, they've-
they've-they've thought that
for...
>> JERRI: For a while?
>> COLBY: Before the merge,
yeah.
>> JERRI: Oh, really.
>> COLBY; And that's been my...
>> JERRI: And you didn't tell
me.
>> COLBY: Oh, I'm sorry.
That's been my only bargain...
That's been my only bargaining
chip.
So, the inevitable came.
I was painted into a corner and-
and had to lie to her to
convince her that there wasn't
anything going on.
I just said, "Look, Jerri, Keith
owes me one on this.
"He and Tina think that the
three of us are going into the
finals," which is the truth,
but Jerri thinks it's just a
ploy.
You and I and Amber still have
complete control of this thing.
>> JERRI: Okay, 'cause I-I was
completely unaware that, at this
point, you were leading Tina and
Keith to believe that it was
going to be the three of you.
>> COLBY: I haven't held led
'em.
They've assumed that.
>> JERRI: Okay.
>> COLBY: Jerri doesn't deserve
to win this thing, if for no
other reason, simply because of
the way she's treated the people
around her.
And that was the biggest
decision when I had to choose
between carrying my plans out
with either Amber and Jerri or
Keith and Tina.
Yeah, everything's cool.
>> JERRI: And this is the deal.
>> AMBER: Do you think it makes
sense?
>> JERRI: No, no, I didn't even,
like, have to talk to him about
that.
>> AMBER: Oh, really?
>> JERRI: Yeah, because he...
>> AMBER: Okay, go.
>> JERRI: He, um, filled me in
on something I was completely
unaware of.
>> COLBY: Yeah. I didn't like
the fact that I had to lie, but
because I was lying to Jerri, I
didn't lose sleep over it.
>> AMBER: Give me a hug.
I really owe you one.
>> COLBY: Are you so full of
food, you can't?
Is that tummy full right now,
there?
>> JERRI: I want a hug.
>> AMBER: The biggest it's ever
been.
>> JERRI: I buy it.
I-I-I believe him, 'cause-'cause
to him... to him, right now,
winning means everything.
So, I mean, I'm... I'm looking
at this whole thing right now
as, yes, we are working as a
team to get to a specific point,
and so that doesn't leave me
feeling very vulnerable at this
point.
>> ALICIA: Oh, boy.
Is that it?
>> NICK: Bits and pieces.
Want to open that?
>> ALICIA: No, let's go.
Let's wait.
>> NICK: Screw them.
Open it now.
>> ALICIA: ( laughs )
Hey, you guys, we got tree mail!
>> NICK: Ah, let see what we got
here.
I love puzzles.
>> ALICIA: A-ha!
One more.
>> NICK: This is the last piece.
Probably just a straight line,
you guys.
"When marking your land, there
can be no doubt."
>> ALICIA: "Just fence off your
spot and keep others out."
>> NICK: "You must plan ahead if
you want to succeed.
It's hip to be square, if it's
immunity you need."
>> ALICIA: Wow.
>> NICK: What can it be?
Very interesting.
Uh, we got tree mail, and, uh,
it says for our immunity
challenge, uh, we got to keep
others out of your land and
fence each... everybody off.
>> AMBER: That is very
interesting.
>> TINA: Cool. What if it's like
one of those...?
>> ALICIA: Whatever you think it
is, think something else.
>> JERRI: Right, right.
Alicia right now is our biggest
threat by far.
She's got the guns, and she out-
strengthens even the men.
The men are sweating it right
now over Alicia, so I think
she... she probably knows that,
and it's probably very important
to her to win immunity right
now.
>> RODGER: Just... just hang in
there and do your best, kiddo.
>> ALICIA: Okay.
>> RODGER: All we can... we can
do.
>> ALICIA: That's it.
>> JEFF: I'll take back the
immunity necklace from you,
Keith.
Put it right back here.
Up for grabs again.
Today's immunity challenge has
nothing to do with age or
strength.
It's all about how you think.
We've created a challenge using
posts and rope.
The object of the game: connect
the ropes to the poles to make
as many squares as possible.
You'll each take turns
connecting one rope at a time.
If it's your rope that completes
the square, you drop a disk in
it, you go again.
Person with the most squares at
the end wins immunity, cannot be
voted out at tonight's Tribal
Council. Ready to go?
Head over here to your disks,
and we'll start.
The order in which you'll take
your turns we determined by
drawing numbers outs of a hat.
Jerri, you're up.
You're going to start it.
Keith.
All right, Amber, you're up.
All right, Tina, you're up.
Okay, Alicia, your turn.
All right, Elisabeth.
Go, Kentucky Joe.
Let's go, Colby.
All right, Nick.
Okay, now it gets a little
harder, 'cause any move you
make's going to either going to
give you a box or set somebody
else up for a run, so choose
wisely.
A gift. First on the board.
Somebody's going to have a good
run in a minute.
Getting tough out there.
>> ALICIA: It's getting tough.
>> ELISABETH: You can all thank
me later.
Nick can thank me now.
>> JEFF: Nick has one.
Amber has one.
>> COLBY: Did you leave Rodger a
square?
>> NICK: No.
>> COLBY: Come on, Rodg, help
your brother out.
>> JEFF: Now you're brothers.
>> RODGER: Yeah.
>> COLBY: Me and Rodg-- we go
way back.
>> RODGER: All family now.
>> COLBY: Four days.
>> JEFF: No box for Rodger.
Let's see what he left for
Colby.
Colby has one.
See if he gets another one.
Colby has two.
>> COLBY: There you go, Jerri.
>> JEFF: Looks like Jerri's on a
run.
Oh, that hurts.
Good run. Six.
Jerri in the lead.
Keith is anxiously awaiting your
next move.
>> JERRI: I'm sure he is.
>> JEFF: Nine.
Keith, you hit the jackpot.
I guess you have Jerri to thank
for that. 15.
>> AMBER: Girl, you set him up.
>> JERRI: Yes, I did.
>> JEFF: 16.
17.
>> KEITH: All good things come
to an end, though.
>> JERRI: I want a massage.
>> JEFF: Good run.
Keith in the lead with 17.
>> JERRI: Whoo!
>> JEFF: Amber, think you can
make a dent in Keith's 17?
>> AMBER: I got 'em all, right?
>> RODGER: Yeah, you got 'em
all.
>> AMBER: Ah, this is killing
me!
>> TINA: It's killing me too.
>> Let's go.
>> AMBER: Oh, you guys.
>> JEFF: Tina has a plan.
14. 15.
16. All right, Tina, you got 16.
Keith's got 17.
You got to find one more spot on
the board.
This is for immunity.
>> TINA: Yep, and I think that's
all of mine.
>> JEFF: Good effort, Tina.
Not good enough.
Mathematically impossible for
Keith to be beat.
Nicely done, Keith.
You get the immunity necklace
again.
Congratulations.
>> TINA: Good job.
>> JEFF: Feels good, doesn't it?
You're getting used to that.
All right, you guys can head
back to camp.
I'll see you tonight at Tribal
Council, where one of you will
be voted out of the tribe.
Somebody's going home tonight.
>> ELISABETH: Lightning.
>> TINA: Whoa, that was close.
( thunder rumbling )
( lightning crashes )
>> RODGER: I love it here in the
Australian outback! Whoo-hoo!
>> KEITH: Mysteriously, every
time we go to Tribal Council, we
have a rainstorm.
I don't know what that means,
but you have to think there's
something working there of
stronger powers than we're aware
of.
>> ALICIA: Elisabeth thinks that
the next vote at Tribal Council
will go for Jerri.
I think Elisabeth is naive in a
lot of ways.
You know, Colby and Keith and
Tina would be foolish to vote
Jerri off.
It would put them at a
disadvantage.
So Nick and I both feel like
it's going to be one of us that
they're targeting.
>> ELISABETH: I'm hoping that
that swing vote to get Jerri off
is Tina.
But I really think Jerri is a
goner tonight.
And I just want to keep playing.
I'm not ready to go home.
I'm not ready to see my friends
go, either.
Tribal Council is going to be
much more interesting than the
last, and... who knows what is
going to happen?
>> JEFF: Always seems to rain at
Tribal Council.
Elisabeth, talk about the tribes
merging, now that you've had a
few days.
Has it been an interesting
dynamic in two different ways of
living coming together now and
forming a new way of living?
>> ELISABETH: It has.
It's been quite interesting.
I mean, I think that we probably
couldn't have done things in a
more opposite way when you look
at the two tribes.
I-I just think that the
differences are known.
I mean, sometimes it's tricky,
and you get used to doing things
your own way, but, um, then you
realize that, well, there might
be a more efficient way also, so
there's been compromise, and I
think it's worked to our benefit
as a group so far.
>> JEFF: What was the reaction
last night, Amber, when you and
Jerri came back with little
bellies from a nice meal?
>> AMBER: It was a very weird
feeling, a guilty kind of
feeling, and I couldn't help but
feel like somewhat of an
outsider for a little while.
>> JEFF: So, what was it like
for you guys not having two
people around last night?
Different feeling, Alicia?
>> ALICIA: It was interesting
going back to camp just having
seven people.
It was, you know, a little
quieter, and everybody was, you
know, kind of contemplating the
situation, and... and our
situation.
Uh, a lot of us had already
resigned ourselves to the fact
that we'd be having rice that
night, so, um... it was... it
was all good.
>> JEFF: Well, you nine have
reached... really the final
phase: the last leg of Survivor.
Someone will be voted out of the
tribe tonight, but they don't go
home.
They become a part of that jury,
and will have a big part in how
this thing plays out, because
the jury will ultimately decide
who the winner is.
You each have, right now, a one
in nine shot at a million bucks.
So, this game is really shifted
now.
The goal is get to the final two
with the goodwill of the other
seven.
Every vote from here on out
counts, so you better think
about that when you're casting
your vote, because the game has
changed.
Let's vote.
Elisabeth, you're first.
>> ELISABETH: Tonight I'm voting
for Jerri.
I just feel it's her time to go,
and she gets really cranky when
she's hungry, and it's bumming
me out a little.
>> AMBER: My vote's for Alicia,
and girl, you're strong inside
and out.
That's the main reason why I
have to vote for you-- because
you're threatening.
So, this is a respect vote, and
I'm going to miss you a lot.
>> RODGER: Nice kid, but way too
loud.
Way too loud.
>> JERRI: Alicia, not only do
you intimidate the hell out of
the women around here, but also
the men.
They are scared to death of you.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
( music playing )
Once the votes are tallied, the
decision is final, the person
will be asked to leave the
Tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Jerri.
Very muscular...
( laughing )
Alicia.
>> ALICIA: Who did that?
Who did that?
>> JEFF: Jerri.
Alicia.
Jerri.
Four votes Jerri, four votes
Alicia.
Final vote...
Alicia, you need to bring me
your torch.
>> ALICIA: Okay.
Listen, bear in mind, be safe,
everybody here.
>> See you in three days.
>> ALICIA: See you all in three
days.
Thank you; thanks, guys.
Thank you, sweetie.
Be good.
>> JEFF: Alicia, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> ALICIA: Bye, guys.
>> JEFF: Grab your torches and
head back to camp.
Good night.
( music playing )
>> ALICIA: I have to say that I
was expecting this.
We knew there was going to be a
threat, and I just hope somebody
from Kucha can take this thing
out and break Ogakor's spirit.
It's all good, though.
Now I get to sit on the jury and
watch everything that happens.
Peace, out.