>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Michael provided fish and took
his leadership role to new
heights.
>> MICHAEL: Dear God, thanks for
making me the leader of the
troops.
>> KIMMI: Mike thanks God for
making him the leader of the
tribe.
I don't know when he was
anointed, but apparently my back
was turned.
>> JEFF: At Ogakor, Kel, the
loner, was the one serious about
fishing.
>> KEL: We do need to get some
fish.
>> KEITH: Our plan for getting
food is, uh... we don't really
have a good plan, actually.
>> JEFF: And Jerry muscled in on
Chef Keith's domain.
>> JERRI: There's a bunch more
things we can have than rice and
I'm ready to start making some
of them.
>> KEITH: She if she wants to
cook some tortillas for
breakfast, I think that's
fantastic.
No worries me.
>> JEFF: Rodger struggled with
the reward challenge.
>> RODGER: Water is not my
finest point.
>> KIMMI: Come on, Rodger!
>> JEFF: At the immunity
challenge, Kimmi, the
vegetarian, secured a victory
for Kucha by swallowing a
mangrove worm, sending Ogakor to
Tribal Counsel were Kel was
voted out.
>> JEFF: Kel, the tribe has
spoken.
14 people are left.
Tonight, one more will go.
game is about the million
dollars, but you need to take
small steps along the way to get
there.
And some of the small steps
along the way to get there are
eating, because none of us are
going to win the million dollars
if we don't have protein in our
bodies and we can win the
challenges.
You guys, there's more food to
be had that we haven't explored
yet.
We still don't have food as a
priority in this camp.
>> RODGER: What's your chances
of catching a pig?
>> JEFF V.: Pig hunting, since
we haven't seen, like, an
abundance of them, you know,
there's like one out there.
>> RODGER: Or any.
>> JEFF V.: You know what I
mean?
We just walk around and hope
that during day we run into this
big pig the size of a table.
Mike wants to go out four hours
a day and look for food because
Mike is hungry.
Nobody else is up for that.
>> MICHAEL: I am going to find
something that's alive that we
are going to kill.
I am very, very determined to
get a pig.
They got to drink sometime and
there's got to be tracks
somewhere and I'm going to
ambush one.
Hey, Jeff, where's that spear
you made?
>> JEFF V.: I didn't finish it.
But if you're going to use it
for a spear, then...
>> MICHAEL: Once I see a pig,
it's going to be a, you know, an
incredible act of exertion to
try and get.
But I'm going to build a spear
with the with the knife on the
end, and then I'm going to run
one down, and I'm going to get
as close as I can.
And I'm just going to kind of,
you know, figure it out from
there.
>> ELISABETH: We should be
looking for tracks right now.
>> ALICIA: This isn't about
running out looking for a hard-
core hunter.
This is about doing something
that's realistic.
That is not realistic.
>> JEFF V.: Mike, I'm a little
worried you're going to lose
that knife.
>> MICHAEL: And I'm glad you
brought that to my attention,
and I will absolutely,
positively not lose this knife.
>> JEFF V.: I hope he loses our
knife, just to give a valuable
reason to go off on the bastard.
>> ELISABETH: We have one knife,
and that one knife, it might as
well be food, but he wants to go
and spear a pig.
Really, have we seen a pig?
We haven't seen a pig.
I haven't seen a pig.
Believe me, if I see a pig, I'll
want to eat it, but to just go
spear just because you want to
come back with one or your
stick and be like "rah, rah"?
I don't know.
>> MICHAEL: This is a pig
killer.
>> JEFF V.: The spear.
The spear, the stupid spear.
"I'm going to go catch pigs."
And he takes our knife and our
rope.
That's classic Mike.
He's an idiot.
I want to see your pig.
Go get me a pig.
( chuckling )
>> TINA: To be honest, I didn't
expect this adventure to be this
hard.
I find myself just craving food.
Doritos.
I want a bag of Doritos more
than anything in the world.
>> COLBY: We haven't had any
meat in a week now, and the lack
of protein hasn't taken its toll
yet, but it's going to.
>> MARALYN: I think I'm going to
go check for messages.
There it is.
Oh, late aboriginal fathers, be
kind to us.
I haven't opened it yet.
"It's time to rise to the top or
make a big flop on your
shoulders will rest the tribe's
fate, for the food you've been
wishing, you only get in damn
fishing, so try not to get
crushed by the wake."
>> JERRI: Sure as hell to be
some fishing line.
Oh, my God.
I think the main thing that's
been keeping us from getting
fish is our fishing line.
So this is a huge reward today.
>> AMBER: I'm worried about
running out of food and running
out of rice.
And we've been trying to eat it
sparingly, but...
>> MARALYN: You got to eat.
>> AMBER: ...it's going to run
out sooner or later.
And I would love to catch a fish
out there or something.
>> KEITH: It's going to be
physical, no matter had you look
at it.
But what we're trying to decide
is if it's a group effort or it
depends on only one person.
And if we have to choose one
person, well, it makes no sense
not to choose, uh, Colby.
He's the strongest, my God.
You're the strongest.
>> COLBY: Yeah, I saw you throw
that one up real quick.
>> KEITH: You got 20 years on
me.
>> MARALYN: A cowboy can handle
any challenge.
>> TINA: He would die before he
would fail us.
>> COLBY: I would like to think
that, win or lose on this deal,
my stock wouldn't fluctuate at
all.
And people can say, "Colby,
don't worry about it.
We don't want to put any
pressure on you if you don't.
If you don't pull through, it's
no big deal."
But internally, I don't think
that's the case.
>> JEFF: Good morning, guys.
Today we got a great challenge.
Before we get to it, though, I
want to show you the reward.
It's an outback fishing package,
complete with line, hooks, lures
and a net.
You got your nylon.
Now that we know what we're
playing for, here's the
challenge.
It tests your strength, balance
and endurance.
The object is for both tribes to
get all these buckets of water
loaded onto the shoulders of the
other tribe's strongest member.
The one who holds the
buckets the longest without
falling or quitting wins.
Each tribe is going to select
one person to be the water
bearer.
It should be your strongest
person.
You're also going to have a
person who is your loader.
This person's going to be
loading the buckets of water
onto the shoulders of your water
bearer.
So when you get out there,
Ogakor will take the water from
Kucha and vice versa, and you
will load it onto your water
bearer.
The rest of the people are going
to transport the water out
there, and you're going to do so
with one of the beams across
your shoulders, a bucket full of
water on either side, and you'll
make your way across the
balancing beams.
If you fall, you got to start
over.
You want as much water in your
buckets as you can handle
because your water is going on
the opposing tribe's water
bearer.
Ogakor, you've chosen Colby to
be your water bearer.
Kucha, you've chosen Michael.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Ogakor! Ogakor! Ogakor!
>> Go, Kucha!
>> RODGER: Hang on, Liz.
Get your balance.
( indistinct conversations )
>> That a girl.
No worries.
>> RODGER: Take your time.
Do your turn.
( cheering )
>> All right, Elisabeth.
Yeah, girl.
>> KEITH: No. No. No.
>> All right, Kimmi.
Good job.
>> Good job.
>> JERRI: Damn it!
>> RODGER: All right, Elisabeth.
Way to go.
>> MICHAEL: Keep it going,
Kucha.
>> That away, Maralyn.
Good job.
>> TINA: That a way, Mad Dog.
( indistinct conversations )
( cheering )
>> Come on, Jeffrey, you got it,
buddy.
>> JEFF: You guys run out of
buckets, it's endurance.
>> MARALYN: Well, take good care
of you tonight, cowboy.
>> Don't even think about that
one.
>> COLBY: This sucks.
This sucks.
>> JEFF: Colby and Michael, you
guys now have all the buckets.
That means you're each holding
more than 400 pounds of water.
Whoever holds on the longest
wins.
>> Let's go, Mike!
( screams )
>> ELISABETH: Let them bring it
on.
You can take ten more, Mike.
You're the man!
Whoo-hoo!
( various shouts )
>> We believe in you, Mike!
( various shouts
of encouragement )
>> JEFF: Hold on.
No decision.
>> ELISABETH: Great job, Mike.
Great job!
>> JEFF: 66 buckets, both these
guys took on their shoulders.
Michael's pole broke before
anybody quit.
That means there's no winner--
so now you guys are going to do
a runoff.
We're going to do a five-minute
timed race.
The tribe that gets the most
buckets on the other tribe's
water bearer's shoulders wins
this.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Nicely done.
>> That a girl.
>> JEFF: You got four minutes.
Eight buckets Ogakor, six
buckets Kucha.
We're all even at ten.
Two minutes.
Kucha, 14.
Ogakor, 12.
20 seconds.
Ogakor up by two.
>> Hang tough. Hang tough.
Make it there, Kimmi.
>> JEFF: Five, four, three, two,
one.
Ogakor!
( cheering )
>> Maralyn!
>> MICHAEL: Let's get out of
here.
I don't want to stay here
anymore.
>> TINA: I can't wait to get the
food you don't have to work your
butt off so to hard to get.
I mean, we have done fantastic
on a small amount of food.
You get food in us, and we're
going to be unstoppable.
>> COLBY: Winning this
competition means a lot more to
us than just bringing home a bag
of fishing supplies.
These are the days when it comes
down to morale, and the mental
edge going into this.
And we're three and one now.
The stats are pretty good for
us.
I certainly don't think this
answers everything.
We still got to catch the fish.
The fish aren't going to jump
into our camp.
>> MITCHELL: At the time, I
didn't think that reward
challenge was very important
because something told me there
really wasn't a lot of fish out
here.
And it sucks that they didn't
give us the fish, they give us
the means to catch the fish.
>> AMBER: You have one.
I saw it.
>> JERRI: Yes, I did. Whoa!
>> MITCHELL: That is awesome.
>> AMBER: I don't know what part
we can touch that he won't slice
us.
>> JERRI: Okay. All right.
>> AMBER: I'm proud of you.
>> MITCHELL: Good job.
>> JERRI: I got it off the hook.
I couldn't stop smiling.
Keith said there were no fish.
He said, "There's no fish out
there."
Him and Kel both were saying
that for days and days.
Holy...
They were practically jumping in
the boat.
>> MITCHELL: Chef Keith, you're
going to be proud of us.
>> KEITH: Here we go now.
We need the fish gutted and
scaled.
When they came back with fish,
they immediately said, "Oh,
where's the chef?"
The "chef" word's never been
used before.
>> MITCHELL: Check that out.
>> KEITH: As a chef, my strategy
was could come in here and
create just spectacular dinners
and meals, and until now, we've
had zero luck at doing anything
from the rivers or from the
floor, for that matter.
>> AMBER: Today is day seven,
and we have caught our first
fish, so actually, that's not
too bad.
It did take us a week, but hey,
it's better than two weeks.
>> KEITH: How did I know that
once the fish is caught, I'd be
the guy filleting these?
>> AMBER: You're doing that
really well.
>> COLBY: Especially with a dull
knife.
He's doing exceptionally well.
>> MITCHELL: Yeah, really.
>> JERRI: I think right now,
everybody's pretty happy that
Keith is there to cook the fish
that we've been catching.
I know sometimes he says things
to other people that kind of rub
them the wrong way, but I'm
probably the one who gets
irritated with him the most.
I'm aware of that.
>> KEITH: Here we go.
We'll just bread those in the
flour, crush up the salt a
little bit.
Put the salt on it and bread it
with the flour.
We just don't have oil, but
it'll be okay.
>> JERRI: I say we don't waste
the flour.
>> COLBY: The most tension in
the tribe seems to be between
Jerri and Keith.
With the cooking and everyone
responding well to her cooking,
( whistles ) that put them on a
level playing field there, and
so there's not really a power
struggle yet, but it could
definitely come to that point.
>> MARALYN: Keith, we're all
hovering over you like a bunch
of greedy sharks.
>> KEITH: Like I'm doing a
cooking class.
>> COLBY: Even when Keith was
over filleting the fish, I
noticed there were several eyes
paying attention, and what that
tells me is that his stock
didn't go up at all.
All he did was basically play
the role of instructor on how to
cook fish.
>> MITCHELL: Ooh, it looks a
little bit like a fish Friday.
>> COLBY: Oh, it smells so good.
>> TINA: Yes, it does, indeedy.
>> AMBER: I can't wait to try
it.
>> KEITH: Maralyn.
>> MITCHELL: After a week of
rice...
>> MARALYN: Oh, wow!
Thank you. Oh, yes.
>> COLBY: Keith, I am so
excited.
>> TINA: That's good.
>> KEITH: You like that?
>> TINA: Yeah.
The fish that Keith made was
excellent.
That was like a blessing 'cause
we were starving.
We were so hungry.
>> MITCHELL: Mmm.
So his first meal wasn't that
great, but his first meal of
fish was fantastic.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God, it is so
good.
>> KEITH: Tonight's dinner was
definitely a success.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> KEITH: Since cooking the
fish, I think my stock's gone up
a good amount.
I think the team has been pretty
excited about what I've been
able to do for them.
>> MITCHELL: It is so good.
I've never had such a great
meal.
But you know what?
Jerri could do that, I could
even do that.
So having a chef out here isn't
as crucial as he may think,
because we don't have a lot to
work with.
>> KIMMI: I'm usually on top of
the water.
I filled up eight jugs this
morning, and now I refilled
up... this is the second one, so
now I've done ten jugs of water.
>> ELISABETH: Are you all right,
Kimmi?
>> KIMMI: Yeah.
It's a lot of work because
you've got to boil this
crocodile creek water before you
can drink it.
You got to go down and fill the
big jug and then go up, boil the
water, let the water cool, put
it in the big container.
I mean, it doesn't seem like
you're contributing a lot
because it's gone, as soon as
it's there, it's gone.
I got to go tend to the water.
>> RODGER: I have noticed the
amount of work that Kimmi has
been doing.
And it seems to be a whole lot
more than really just about
anybody else.
She's really worried that she's
going to be the next one to go.
>> KIMMI: I sometimes feel
vulnerable because I don't have
a tight, tight bond with
somebody that could be pulling
for me in my corner.
Yeah, that might be a bad thing
because I might be just like,
"Oh, easy target, pick Kimmi
off."
This means that I boiled
everything in this jug.
>> MICHAEL: Really?
>> ALICIA: Every job and task
that Kimmi takes on in this camp
can be taken over by somebody
else, for sure.
>> KIMMI: Kentucky?
>> RODGER: Yes, ma'am, what?
Do you have lotion?
You all good?
>> RODGER: Yeah, I just put some
on a little while ago, thanks.
>> JEFF V.: Well, there's sort
of a little battle between
Kentucky Joe and Kimmi.
Some of the people in the tribe
feel that we will be stronger
without Kentucky Joe.
>> RODGER: I'm going to try to
catch some fish this morning.
Make a new line.
>> ELISABETH: I know in the
beginning there was talk of
voting Rodger off and I tried
really hard to rally people not
to do it just 'cause I feel
strongly for him.
>> ALICIA: Kentucky Joe, though
he's not a strong member of this
tribe as far as challenges are
concerned, he knows what he's
doing outside.
>> RODGER: If I can draw them,
maybe I'll be able to catch one
this time.
I always heard that the best
place to catch them is where a
stream runs into a river.
I was out here looking for
sinkers to make a new fishing
pole with, and I found a little
rock out here about that tall
shaped like a heart.
>> ELISABETH: He said here you
go.
What's that look like?
And I said, "a heart."
He said, "You take that with
you, give it to your boyfriend
when you get back."
And he said, "You just know I
care."
And it just... it just touched
me.
Thanks a lot.
>> RODGER: You're welcome.
Me and her, it just seemed like
we hit it off right off the bat.
>> ELISABETH: You're so sweet.
>> RODGER: Well, thank you.
You're a sweet little gal, too,
I tell you what.
Your parents got a lot to be
proud of with you.
>> ALICIA: Elisabeth said she
won't vote off Kentucky Joe, and
she protects him.
>> ELISABETH: It matters so much
to me that he's around, so I'm
not writing his name down.
Uh-uh.
I will not spell that man's
name.
>> TINA: Hey, you, girly girl.
>> MARALYN: Hello.
>> TINA: I just followed your
voice.
>> MARALYN: Was it that loud?
>> TINA: Maralyn, she's kind of
like our little song bird and
our little cheerleader in our
camp, so Maralyn and I have
bonded more so than I have with
any of the other people.
It might be our ages, it might
be that we just kind of took up
for one another.
Mad Dog?
Nothing hurts Mad Dog?
>> MARALYN: Tina is a fabulous
woman.
She is a star.
I trust Tina the most.
Um, I do not trust Jerri.
>> COLBY: You like crunchy
peanut butter or creamy?
>> JERRI: Crunchy.
>> COLBY: Got to have crunchy.
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> COLBY: Black coffee or cream
and sugar?
>> JERRI: Cream and sugar.
>> AMBER: There could be
something going on between Jerri
and Colby.
I mean from the very first day,
she told me how cute she thought
he was.
And at first she didn't think
that he liked her.
And I was are like, "Jerri, it's
only the second day."
>> JERRI: I'd really like it if
Colby and I got together.
He's exactly my type, plus,
he's a cowboy and I'm such a
sucker for cowboys.
>> COLBY: Cake or ice cream?
>> JERRI: Oh, cake.
>> COLBY: Oh... I dig ice cream.
Oh, Jerri, Jerri and I are
getting along great.
Every day we have more fun
flirting with each other and
seeing how far we can kind of
push it.
Chocolate chip cookie or oatmeal
raisin?
>> JERRI: Chocolate chip.
>> COLBY: That wasn't really a
fair competition.
Oatmeal raisin never stood a
chance in that battle.
>> KEITH: Oh, I think Jerri is
legitimately attracted to Colby.
But I'm sure that strategic play
is involved, there's no
question.
>> COLBY: You don't have to give
me a massage...
>> JERRI: That's all right,
though.
I really, I don't mind,
especially after today,
what you did to your back.
>> KEITH: I think Jerri's
approach is just a lot of... she
wants to really feel important.
She's already got Colby on her
side, but she gets on his side
rubbing his back and, you know,
nuzzling at night, you know,
that whole thing, sharing the
blanket, all that kind of
stuff.
So it's natural for Colby just
to gravitate and a little smoke
screen goes up and so he doesn't
necessarily see certain things.
Or maybe he does and I'm just
not aware of it.
( Colby moans, Jerri laughs )
>> COLBY: At this point, I'm not
sure if Jerri has ulterior
motives.
Jerri is very capable of
deceiving me or anyone else in
the tribe.
And maybe she's not.
Maybe I'm wrong, but, uh, I
still can't let my guard down.
>> JERRI: Relax.
If it came down to me having to
vote for Colby.... I would.
>> ALICIA: This is spear grass.
See how tall that is?
>> JEFF V.: Yeah, that's
definitely spear grass.
>> ALICIA: That is spear grass.
>> JEFF V.: Alicia and I, we
went for that foraging walk
together intentionally.
I've thought a lot about the
voting, and I wanted to be able
to get away with her and just
have her think about the future
and who would be the most
valuable to have with us in a
final four, that we could beat.
You and I committed to each
other for that final four.
>> ALICIA: Right, because the
truth of the matter is, I feel
like you're the only one that I
really trust, at this point.
Wow!
Look at the size of that one.
>> JEFF V.: That is a major
spider.
>> ALICIA: Jeff and I are
constantly scheming and planning
about how this thing should go.
>> JEFF V.: Now, Elisabeth can't
be in the final four.
>> ALICIA: She can't be because
she'll make it to the end.
>> JEFF V.: No. And I don't
think Nick can be either.
We talked about, you know, who
we're going to vote for now, who
we're going to vote for next
time, who we trust, who we don't
trust.
>> ALICIA: Nick flies under the
radar.
>> JEFF V.: Nick flies very much
under the radar, and Nick is a
total player.
I don't trust him as far as I
can spit.
I mean, I feel Nick would screw
all of us.
Nick is very lazy.
Don't let me take the fire with
me, as I drag this through here.
He won't pick up anything, he
won't lift anything.
If you ask him to help you,
he'll act like he doesn't hear
you.
>> NICK: I'm sorry.
I didn't even hear what you
said.
>> JEFF V.: That's okay.
>> NICK: I'm zoning out.
>> ALICIA: You know what?
He's too secure in his position
right now.
>> JEFF V.: Yeah, absolutely.
He's done our kitchen, which
is lovely.
And he's built a lovely little
outdoor chair and he's built a
lovely little patio but only
because he doesn't want to do
anything else.
>> NICK: Mentally, you need to
feel like you're comfortable
where you are.
And that's why I built the
kitchen.
You know, the kitchen serves
little purpose, but it looks
good, it makes you feel
comfortable.
It's noticeable that you're
doing work, which makes people
happy.
>> ELISABETH: Nice!
>> NICK: Hey, I made you a
recliner, Rodger.
>> RODGER: Hey, you get that
done where I can sleep in it.
>> KIMMI: I just don't see the
necessity in making benches when
we need firewood.
I think that that's not a
priority, I think that's is a
luxury.
>> JEFF V.: Unfortunately, we
need him, so, you know, what can
we do?
He's one of our stronger people,
but when we get to a point where
somebody in our group has to go,
he's going to be the first.
( thunder rumbling )
>> MITCHELL: When it rains, it's
a scary moment.
If the fire goes out, everything
around us gets wet, and we only
have a couple matches.
>> JERRI: It was at the point
where it was almost out, and
there was hardly any light
coming off of it.
And no heat at all.
>> KEITH: Do you have some of
that grass?
It was really raining hard.
We were not going to let the
rain win over our fire.
It just wasn't going to happen.
>> TINA: I'm tired.
That was a rough one.
Cold, rainy, pretty miserable.
>> MITCHELL: My side of the tent
was all wet, so I had to sleep
in wet clothes with a wet
blanket and sand, and I can't
recall sleeping even a full
hour.
>> MARALYN: Last night was a
hard night.
It poured, I mean not just a
little drizzle, it just poured.
>> KEITH: People fight,
sometimes, to put the fire out.
We were up all night trying to
keep that fire going.
I think the hardest thing for
me, so far, has just been trying
to catch up enough sleep so the
body's ready to go into combat
in our challenges.
>> JERRI: Everybody's kind of
getting a little lethargic.
The fish definitely helped.
That was a big morale booster,
but ever since, we're kind of on
a downslide right now and it
kind of scares me a little bit.
>> MITCHELL: When you think
about how low you are on
nutrition and how hungry you
are, being tired just... just
quadruples it.
Getting mail is always an
exciting thing, but I was so
weak walking up that hill to get
the mail, it was treacherous for
me.
And I knew, I knew that, inside,
there would be a challenge that
I may not be able to do, and
that was a depressing thought
for me.
We got mail.
>> COLBY: Sweet!
>> JERRI: Percussion!
>> MITCHELL: "I think that
you'll find that your tribe's
in a bind,
between a hard place
and a rock.
But if you work as a team,
it's not as hard as it seems.
Pull together and you'll win as
a lock."
>> JERRI: Ropes-- maybe tug of
war?
>> COLBY: Bind in here, which
means maybe something's bound
with ropes.
>> AMBER: Maybe we're all going
to be tied up or something.
>> COLBY: "Rock and a hard
place," it's probably going to
have to do with rocks.
>> MITCHELL: Gosh... I'm a
little weak for climbing rocks.
>> COLBY: It's not the time to
be weak, brother.
>> MITCHELL: I know.
>> COLBY: I'm dragging.
This is the most tired I've
been.
Personally, I'm a little worried
about myself.
I know I'm not going to be as
strong going into this one as I
have been in the past.
>> JEFF: Come on down, guys.
Welcome to your toughest
challenge yet on Survivor.
Let me get that immunity idol.
Today's challenge is very simple
in concept and very tough in
execution.
It's an obstacle course.
You're going to start by racing
through a log chute, then
you'll go down a steep sand
slide into the river.
On the other side, you'll go
through a series of obstacles.
Then, finally, you're going to
sprint across the sand to the
finish line.
It's going to require a lot of
physical endurance, flexibility,
and teamwork, because here's the
twist: you're going to go
tethered as a team.
( laughter, groaning )
>> JEFF V.: Oh, God!
>> JEFF: You're only as fast as
your slowest member.
>> AMBER: Wow!
>> JEFF: If somewhere along the
way, a tribe member can't go any
longer, you can carry them.
But they have to finish.
The first tribe to get all their
members across the finish line
wins immunity.
Here we go, guys.
Survivors ready...
Go!
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
>> Good, good, good, good!
Good, good...
Good... good...
>> Come on, back there.
Come on, come on, come on...
>> Good, good, good.
>> Look out, look out, look out.
>> Go, go, go!
>> Come on, come on, come on!
>> Hang on, hang on, hang on.
>> Wait, wait, wait...
>> Go, go, go!
>> Go, go! We got it! We got it!
>> Wait!
>> Don't pull, don't pull.
>> You gotta ease up a little.
Careful...
>> Go, go!
>> Dig deep, dig deep, dig deep!
>> Go, pick it up, pick it up!
>> Come on, come on.
>> Go... go...
>> Come on!
>> Come on now!
>> Go!
( indistinct shouts )
>> Come on! Come on!
( indistinct shouting )
>> Go, go, go!
Pick up your feet!
>> Stay on your feet...
Stay on your feet, guys.
>> JEFF: Right here's the
finish!
>> Ouch!
>> Stand up and walk!
>> JEFF: Last member across!
Last member across!
>> Watch the table...
>> Everybody...
>> JEFF: Kucha!
( cheering )
>> Immunity!
>> ELISABETH: Good job!
>> Good job, guys.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God!
Good job, good job!
Oh, my God...
>> JEFF V.: Yeah!
( whooping )
( trilling )
( all gasping, muttering )
>> JEFF: Kucha, this is yours.
You want this, Jeff?
>> Oh, my God!
( whooping, cheering )
>> JEFF: Ogakor, you guys know
what I'm here to tell you.
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Tribal council, one of
you guys will be going home.
>> KIMMI: You guys always said,
when it comes to teamwork and
heart, Kucha's got it.
>> ELISABETH: Kucha's got it.
>> KEITH: Our last immunity
challenge was a real tough one.
Mad Dog Maralyn, you know, she
had a difficult time.
>> MITCHELL: Had we voted for
Maralyn last week, and not Kel,
I can almost guarantee you we'd
have immunity right now.
>> COLBY: She's ready.
She'll be very understanding.
>> TINA: We're going to need
Keith.
>> TINA: The mood in the camp is
a sad mood, but it's also a very
strategic move.
Everybody's thinking, "Who's
thinking what?"
>> JERRI: There's been five of
us: myself, Colby, Mitchell,
Amber and Tina, who've kind of
decided to all vote the same.
>> KEITH: My vote's not going
towards Maralyn.
We've had a lot of physical
challenges up till now, but I'm
sure some of them are going to
be mental, and I think Maralyn
could prove to be an asset.
Why should we lose her?
For what, 'cause she fell a few
times, 'cause she's older?
Why?
What kind of team is that?
She works her ass off.
She's the first one up every
morning-- you, me and her.
Mitchell does all right, but he
struggles.
He doesn't do a lot of work.
When was the last time you've
seen him go up the hill and get
wood?
Never.
Mitchell's the weakest of our
strength of getting a lot of
heavy work done.
When it comes to the challenges,
Maralyn, I think, is stronger
than he is in the challenges.
All we need is just the four of
us.
No pressure.
>> TINA: Thanks, Keith.
>> KEITH: I could be cutting my
own throat doing this.
At least with Colby, we can
discuss it, probably disagree
upon it and it'll stay with us.
>> COLBY: Keith's wanting to put
you on the chopping block
tonight.
And he's got Maralyn with him
and he came to me and Tina.
Strategies are starting to
develop more and go in different
directions, and the more we
learn about each other, the more
you start to second-guess what
you've done.
>> MITCHELL: Keith is trying to
pull around a swing vote to try
to get me out.
Why would we want to kick off
our fun Maralyn and then keep
the pessimist and the back-
stabber?
>> KEITH: You guys ready?
>> COLBY: At this point,
Keith and Mitchell and Maralyn
are neck-and-neck for tribal
council tonight.
>> JEFF: So let's talk about the
fact that you guys have been
here... nine days?
>> MARALYN: Yes.
>> JEFF: You're in the honeymoon
stage.
It hasn't even begun yet.
So I just want to talk about a
couple of big topics: trust.
Colby, is there anybody here
that you don't trust, that you
wouldn't trust?
>> COLBY: Sure. Sure.
>> JEFF: Tell me about that.
>> COLBY: Well, I think that's
part of the game.
It's way too early to tell
exactly who you can trust, I
think.
>> JEFF: What about you,
Mitchell?
You trust everybody here for 42
days?
>> MITCHELL: Well, I think the
motto is "trust no one."
I have a lot of faith in a good
number of these people, but I
couldn't give 100% of my trust.
>> JEFF: What about you, Mad
Dog?
Are these all your buddies?
>> MARALYN: Yes.
Yes, and Jeff, I trust with my
heart.
>> JEFF: Jerri, who here would
you say you're closest to,
so far?
>> JERRI: Um... I've been very
fortunate in my ability to bond
with Amber and Mitchell and
Colby, in particular.
I think friendship does enter
into it at some point, but it's
very important to keep that
separate from the game.
It's two totally different
things, and that's where it gets
tricky.
>> JEFF: Keith, who have you
bonded with?
>> KEITH: Several individuals.
You know, and I guess I equate
the bonding different than
friendship.
I think it's more of a
camaraderie for me than it is
actual friendship.
>> MARALYN: Jeff, I'm conjoined
with Tina.
>> JEFF: Really?
>> MARALYN: Yes.
( Jerri laughs )
>> MARALYN: She is a
constellation.
And... the cowboy.
Yeah.
Oh, the poor cowboy has dragged
me around so many times.
>> COLBY: I'd do it again.
>> MARALYN: I appreciate it,
Cowboy.
You hear that, he'd do it again?
>> COLBY: I'd do it again.
>> JEFF: Colby, are you sad at
all tonight?
>> COLBY: Yeah, yeah, I am.
Because any way the vote goes on
this, the seven of us are really
tight, so the inevitable is
here.
We're broken up after tonight,
and that's tough.
No matter which way it goes.
>> JEFF: It's time to vote.
Mad Dog, you're up first.
>> KEITH: Mitchell, it just
seems like you're tired.
>> JERRI: This is probably one
of the most difficult things for
me to do right now.
It's purely strategic.
It's nothing personal.
I am going to miss you dearly.
>> TINA: Mad Dog, I love you, I
value your friendship more than
anything.
This vote has everything to do
with a promise I made.
It has nothing to do with you.
I hope you'll understand.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are tallied,
the decision is final, and the
person will be asked to leave
the tribal council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
The first vote...
Jerri.
Maralyn.
Mitchell.
Mad Dog.
Three votes, Mad Dog.
And a very sad Mad Dog.
You need to bring me your torch,
Mad Dog.
Mad Dog, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Bye.
>> JEFF: Well, I don't think I
have to ask how you guys are
feeling tonight.
I think the last vote probably
says it all.
Grab your torches, head back
to camp.
Stay tuned for scenes from
next time, and Maralyn's
final words.
Next time on Survivor:
Will Keith and Tina wage war
against Jerri?
>> KEITH: I didn't come out here
to be pushed around by a
bartender wanna-be actress.
( raspy laughter )
>> JEFF: And at Kucha, has
Michael's blood lust gone too
far?
>> KIMMI: Oh, my God, oh, my
God, oh, my God...
>> ALICIA: We've reached a new
level.
>> MICHAEL: If I go out, I'm
going out full.
( wry laughter )
>> MARALYN: I cannot thank you
enough for selecting me, and
this experience has meant so
much to me.
At 52, I could feel myself
really coming alive.
Oh, hell, I'm tired.
Did this all really happen?
Did I... did I do this?