>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
with Jerri gone, Amber was on
her own.
>> KEITH: She's kind of a lone
lamb.
I think Amber made a tactical
mistake by staying tight with
Jerri.
>> JEFF: The food situation was
desperate.
>> AMBER: This is how much rice
we have left to last us 14 days.
>> JEFF: And the tribe was
running on empty.
>> ELISABETH: I feel so weak.
I'm feeling terrible.
>> JEFF: The rising waters were
a growing threat to the
Barramundi camp.
>> ELISABETH: A storm could come
and just wash our tent right
out.
It's right in line with the
riverbed.
>> JEFF: At the immunity
challenge, Colby's dwindling
strength didn't stop him from
winning the talisman.
( Colby yelling )
>> JEFF: Back at camp, the tribe
was offered more food.
You've got 13 days left, and I
don't think you're going to make
it.
But it came with a hefty price.
I need something of value.
I'm talking camp: your tarps and
that Texas flag.
>> TINA: I think it was a fair
trade.
There's worse things in life
than being wet, such as starving
to death.
>> JEFF: At tribal council,
Jerri and Alicia returned as
members of the jury, and Nick
was voted out.
Six remain.
Who will be the next to go?
>> ELISABETH: This game, in the
past three days, has become
drastically primal.
We are just beings out here that
need food.
>> AMBER: The servings are so
small.
It's, like, maybe four
spoonfuls.
>> ELISABETH: It's turned into a
nightmare, all of a sudden.
You just can't think about it.
The things that are important
have become really clear here.
You know, you shed yourself of
all excess, and we just gave up
our shelter for food.
And that is a pretty, pretty
extreme situation.
>> AMBER: When we got our new
rice, we decided we needed to be
very, very careful with it this
time.
The risk of losing it again just
wasn't going to be an option.
So we measured out the rice cup
by cup by cup by cup.
This is the least amount of rice
we've ever had.
>> TINA: No wonder we're all so
weak and tired.
This is all we're living on.
>> ELISABETH: Anyone want some
scrapings from the pot?
>> COLBY: Oh, sure.
>> TINA: That rice gave me hope
that I was not going to have to
be out here starving to death
for the next 11 days, which, to
be honest, that's what I thought
was going to occur.
>> AMBER: Hope factors in a huge
amount for your existence here.
I mean, you always have to hope
for the next day to come, hope
for a fish, a nice night with no
rain.
And I just keep hoping that the
next three days to come, I'm
still here and the next three
days to come that I'm still
here.
>> ELISABETH: Keith, Colby and
Tina are three together.
And they see Amber, although
she's grown a lot, they don't
see that she is a strong person.
>> TINA: Amber's a sweet girl,
but you can't get by just on
flying below the radar.
She never really proved to me
that she could stand on her own
two feet.
Now, she has proved to me that
she's a tougher little girl than
I made her out to be.
>> ELISABETH: The people who are
in control are basically going
to push your eject button one
time or another.
And you just hope it's not the
next time.
>> COLBY: Rodger and Elisabeth
both know that we brought them
along this entire time with the
intent to eliminate them before
we eliminate ourselves.
And they are well aware of the
fact that they've got to win
immunity in order to stick
around.
>> ELISABETH: The next
challenges are very important to
me.
Reward and immunity.
I don't care how hungry and weak
I am, there's no holding me
back.
I need them.
>> JEFF: How are you feeling?
>> RODGER: Good.
>> TINA: All right.
>> JEFF: Okay, today's challenge
is for a reward.
It's a ropes course, and it's
designed to be confusing.
It's a jungle rope maze.
You'll have four checkpoints
along the way.
At each checkpoint, there are
several ropes that lead either
directly or indirectly to the
next one.
We'll have two carabiners.
One carabiner needs to be
attached to your rope at all
times.
So, whenever you change ropes,
you take the other carabiner
that's free, clip to the new
rope, then unclip from the
existing rope.
First person to reach all four
checkpoints, get to the finish,
wins the reward.
The reward is a food reward with
a twist.
Yo, come on in!
As you know, in the Outback...
Yeah, lots of cattle, lots of
cattle ranches.
Stockmen-- Australian cowboys--
are the guys who take care of
the cattle.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
>> ELISABETH: Oh, look at how
beautiful.
>> JEFF: You're going to saddle
up on a horse with these guys,
spend the night.
You'll have a trek through the
Outback on horseback, you'll go
back to their camp, have some
authentic stockman grub.
What are you having?
What's for dinner tonight?
>> Beef cubes, beans and bread
and butter...
>> JEFF: All the Bud Light you
can drink to go with that?
Sounds good.
What about breakfast?
>> You can have some bacon and
eggs for breakfast.
>> AMBER: Oh, God.
>> JEFF: You'll also have a cot
to sleep on.
>> AMBER: Wow.
That's a good reward.
>> JEFF: Let's head to the game.
We'll see you guys at the end.
Thanks.
>> AMBER: Bye.
>> ELISABETH: Bye.
>> JEFF: Let's go.
>> JEFF: Survivors ready?
Go!
>> JEFF: Almost there!
Keep going, Amber.
He's wearing down.
Nice job.
( Amber groaning )
Way to go, Rodger.
You're coming in for the bronze.
That-a-way, Rodg.
>> AMBER: Way to go, Tina.
>> JEFF: Way to finish,
Elisabeth.
You got it, girl.
>> TINA: Go, girl!
All the way!
>> JEFF: That-a-way, Chef.
Finish strong.
Colby, come here.
I want to give you a little
taste of some of the food you're
going to have tonight.
They call this damper.
No, it's for him.
>> COLBY: Can I give it to them?
>> JEFF: No.
I'm sorry, you can't.
>> TINA: Thanks, Colby.
That's okay, Colby.
>> JEFF: This is just a little
sample here.
Take a little bite of this.
They make this up all the time.
Good stuff?
You can take this on your
horseback ride.
The boys are waiting for you
just up ahead.
>> TINA: Enjoy it.
>> RODGER: Have fun.
>> JEFF: Have a good time, man.
See you tomorrow.
>> COLBY: Thanks, guys.
>> ELISABETH: You tell us all
about it.
>> RODGER: Put some pork and
beans in your pocket to bring
back.
>> TINA: Get strong.
We'll miss you tonight.
>> COLBY: I'm ready.
( thunder rumbling )
( thunder booms )
>> COLBY: The storm hit about
ten minutes into the ride.
We went right into the face of
the storm, and that kind of
startled the horses a little
bit.
( horse whinnies )
Heavy, heavy, heavy winds.
You couldn't see anything around
you.
It felt like hail, the raindrops
were coming down so hard.
There was so much water running,
it really looked like there was
water running uphill.
It was bad stuff.
Worse than any storm I've ever
been through.
I feel sorry for all those guys
that had to go back to a very
wet Barramundi Beach.
>> RODGER: Wow, how fast did
that come?
>> KEITH: Unbelievable.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh.
>> AMBER: This is unbelievable.
>> ELISABETH: This is... all
this weather happened in an
hour.
We came across here, and there
was one puddle.
>> KEITH: Let's hope our
riverbed didn't get flooded like
this.
Our camp is gone.
>> RODGER: After seeing this,
where we've got our camp is
called a dry creek bed.
I doubt it if it's dry right
now.
>> TINA: The thing is, I don't
know how we're going to get
across.
>> RODGER: It's going to be a
good while before we get across
here.
We're talking some hours here.
We had to wait two or three
hours till the creeks had gone
down.
( thunder rumbling )
Everybody had kind of quit
talking, but I knew what was on
everybody's mind.
Everybody was thinking what's
going to be left back there when
we get back there.
>> RODGER: We're okay, girls,
I think.
>> KEITH: Don't jump to
conclusions.
>> RODGER: Oh, gosh.
>> AMBER: We have barely
anything.
>> RODGER: Oh, gosh.
When I first come down the
bank there, I could see
some blankets hanging on the
line, I thought, oh,
everything's okay.
Then I walked another 20 feet,
where I could see on over,
and I could see that everything
wasn't okay.
It looked like a small hurricane
or something went through there.
>> AMBER: Wow...
>> RODGER: It's here, but
barely.
I hope the rice is here.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
>> RODGER: Where was the rice
can?
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
>> AMBER: I don't know where the
rice can was at!
>> RODGER: Don't worry about it.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh...
>> RODGER: The rice tin was
right over here.
>> AMBER: The rice tin probably
washed away.
>> ELISABETH: It looks like the
rice is gone, you guys.
>> RODGER: No supper.
>> ELISABETH: Whoa.
We were really wondering if we'd
get back here and find our dry
riverbed not so dry, and...
despite all optimism and
hope, our entire campsite was
washed out.
>> AMBER: Looks like a tornado
went through here.
>> RODGER: The rice is gone,
our knives are gone...
>> TINA: Absolutely incredible.
>> RODGER: Where's our fishing
tackle?
>> ELISABETH: Gone.
Everything that was on that box,
that table.
>> RODGER: Yeah, we had the
hooks right up in there.
>> KEITH: That water came
through like a flurry and just
took everything with it.
It was just... there was no way
to describe it.
Especially when we're out here
with so little, and we lost
everything.
>> TINA: I walked down the hill
and I saw the devastation.
And my first thought was, you
know, that's our home.
>> RODGER: Let's just see if
some of that stuff may have been
stuck in here.
>> TINA: Washed away our food,
our cooking, our knives,
everything.
Everything's just gone.
And to be honest, I was just
really, really mad.
I don't know who I was mad at or
what I was mad at.
I was just angry.
>> ELISABETH: We have no food.
>> AMBER: No, none.
We can't even fish.
We don't have any fishing rods.
We haven't eaten all day.
( thunder rumbilng )
>> COLBY: That challenge-and-
reward combination was tailor-
made for me.
Hey, Jeff!
>> JEFF: You look like you
would were born to ride.
>> COLBY: We've been having a
great time.
To be able to jump on horseback
and go ride out to a camp with a
bunch of cowboys and sit around
a campfire and eat beans and
beef stew.
I mean, that's something I would
do at home.
Thank you very much.
>> You're welcome.
>> COLBY: Oh, man, this is so
good.
>> JEFF: So how do you assess
your shot now:
Nine days tomorrow, when you go
back.
You're obviously going to have a
leg up, because right now, this
food's going to give you a lot
of energy.
>> COLBY: Well, physically,
maybe, you have a leg up.
Politically, you're a leg down,
especially because this is my
second reward in a row.
You know, inevitably there's got
to be some resentment there.
And a lot of that goes through
your head.
You think of the politics, you
think, well, do I pull up five
feet and let Amber win this...
>> JEFF: Really!
>> COLBY: And then you... you
just say no.
You are here to win, you're here
to compete.
And it may happen.
I may get voted off in the next
couple of tribal councils and if
does, I'm going to be glad I ate
this tonight.
I feel just about as fortunate
as I have in 33 days to be able
to not only get a warm hot meal
but also get a warm dry bed to
sleep in.
>> JEFF: Colby, final cheer.
I'm going to down this.
I'm gonna leave you.
>> COLBY: Thanks, Jeff.
It's a very bittersweet time,
when you realize what you're
doing.
Virtually, what I'm doing by
enjoying coffee and enjoying a
cot is taking that opportunity
away from somebody else.
>> This song's called "Drinking
Beer With Your Mates."
♪ So set the drinks up, barman
'Cause I've only got one day
♪ And keep 'em comin'
Talk fast, and wind will
blow our bay
♪ At night, around our campfire,
It's great to listen there
The stories get a whole better
When you've got a heap of
beer... ♪
>> COLBY: Yeah!
>> AMBER: When I got back to the
camp, we didn't really have much
to say to each other because we
were all just devastated.
>> KEITH: I'm going to go
further down because that food
should float, you know?
>> ELISABETH: The stuff could be
caught, dragged under here.
Well, Tina and Keith thought of
going downriver and seeing if
they can find something that
washed up on shore.
>> KEITH: So I just walked the
riverbank and realized that on
the other side, our tin of food
was there.
It was still sealed.
>> TINA: We can cross down
here, where the current's not so
strong and go across the bank.
>> KEITH: That's a little deep
there.
>> TINA: It may be deep.
You're going to try to cross
this current?
You're crazy.
Trust me, you can't cross that.
You'll slip.
>> KEITH: I'd rather try that.
>> RODGER: Well, be careful out
in that current.
I wasn't so much worried about
him getting knocked down off the
log on into the river.
I was worried about him falling
backwards.
You want a rope or something to
put around you?
I was afraid he'd get swept down
underneath that log and get
caught on some limbs down
underneath there, and there'd
have been no way in the world
anybody would have been able to
get him out of there.
>> TINA: Keith, how do you think
you're going to get it back
across?
>> RODGER: You'll never make it.
>> TINA: I went on downriver.
I think Keith was trying to
cross the wrong way.
I saw that the current was
strong... your adrenaline gets
pumping, and you just know:
I can do anything.
>> AMBER: Keith... oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God.
>> AMBER: Tina's across, Keith!
Keith come back!
Oh, they're making me
so nervous.
>> ELISABETH: I just don't want
to take my eyes off them.
>> RODGER: If you can't bring it
all, just bring one plastic bag
of it over or something.
Leave the can over there.
Throw it behind you, and the
rapids will bring it right down
to you.
Ready?
Watch this turn-- that current.
>> KEITH: Ready?
>> TINA: Yeah.
>> RODGER: Y'all surprised me.
I wouldn't have thought the
chance of finding that was one
in 10,000.
>> AMBER: I don't know how you
guys saw that.
>> KEITH: Our food.
>> RODGER: I can't believe the
lid stayed on that thing.
>> ELISABETH: You guys are...
you are amazing.
>> RODGER: Hey, good job, buddy.
>> You make me want to cry.
>> RODGER: Tina, good job.
>> TINA: Thank you.
>> RODGER: One heck of a job.
>> AMBER: Thank you so much.
We're going to start a fire,
Tina, we're going to get you
warmed up.
>> TINA: We were very hungry.
It's the thing that we feel most
out here.
And there was nothing that would
keep me from getting that rice
can.
It's just survival of the
fittest, and I want to eat,
plain and simple.
I want the rice.
>> KEITH: Food's everything to
us at this stage.
Geez, we gave up our shelter for
our food.
Then we lose it in the rain?
That's not going to happen.
>> RODGER: Hey, Keith, do we
have our matches?
>> KEITH: No.
They got wet.
They were there in my coat.
And the coat got wet.
They're wet.
>> RODGER: We got the rice and
no fire.
>> AMBER: We were cold and we
were wet.
And we were thinking at least we
can light a fire and dry off.
And we had no way of starting
the fire.
It was just devastating.
I mean, it's like nothing else
could have gone wrong.
>> RODGER: I'd suggest to
anybody who don't have on dry
clothes needs to be doing it
before dark falls here, 'cause
we're all going to be freezing
tonight.
>> You can look forward to a
good warm night's sleep, eh,
Colb?
>> COLBY: Oh, man.
The cot, yeah.
Breakfast in the morning.
>> Bacon and eggs.
>> COLBY: Golly.
( laughing )
I'm going to have to pace myself
a little better than I did
tonight.
I dug in too fast tonight.
I was hungry and I dove in.
And the first plate I had just
went straight through me.
I felt awful.
We were so used to eating
nothing but rice out here.
My stomach just, it twisted and
turned.
As soon as that second or third
spoonful went in, I knew it was
going to be trouble.
>> You couldn't help it?
>> COLBY: It went through me,
man.
I just, I couldn't help it.
It's been too long since I've
had any good food.
>> ELISABETH: This is Survivor,
you guys.
This is the stuff that you just
didn't plan for.
>> RODGER: You can't begin to
tell anybody back home what
you've been through.
>> AMBER: You can't even
describe this.
>> RODGER: No.
>> AMBER: It's something you
can't even describe.
>> RODGER: Survivor is
definitely real.
>> AMBER: This is no longer a
game.
This is...
>> RODGER: This is, this is...
>> AMBER: No, this is life right
now.
>> COLBY: Unequivocally the best
peanut butter and jelly I've
ever had in my life.
I'm stuffed already.
We hadn't even broken into the
bacon and eggs, and I don't give
a damn.
I'm going to eat as much as I
can here and then I'm going to
go sit by the fire and eat as
much as I can over there.
I may have to stop and use the
bathroom four times on the way
back to camp, and it doesn't
matter.
Mm...
( sizzling )
>> Hey, Colby, how do you want
your eggs, mate?
Didn't you say you wanted them
fairly runny?
>> COLBY: Yeah.
I appreciated the opportunity to
eat incredibly.
Just the opportunity, no matter
how sick it made me and no
matter how sick I feel now.
I had that choice.
I had the choice to eat, and eat
and eat.
I'm very fortunate.
Boy, that's good, Pedro.
Bacon, eggs, perfect.
The beans are good.
Mm...
>> KEITH: That was the most
miserable night in my entire
life.
I can now say that.
I will never have a more
miserable night.
I hope not.
>> ELISABETH: We just have to
make sure that tonight's a
little more safe from the
weather than last night.
Building a shelter.
This is our first priority right
now.
>> TINA: Hey, Rodger, the sand's
actually dry in there, in our
thing.
>> AMBER: Are we thinking of
staying down there?
>> KEITH: Right there at the top
of the ridge.
Nothing to build a little
shelter.
>> RODGER: I had laid awake all
night thinking about the
shelter.
And I definitely did not want to
put it back down there on that
sand.
>> TINA: There's no good place
to hide here.
It's very frustrating.
Where the heck do we build it,
you know?
In the river bed where it's
going to flood or up on the high
point where we can get struck by
lightning?
>> RODGER: If we can get the
roof on it the first thing, get
it like we want it, we can
at least get underneath that
tonight.
>> COLBY: I think this is the
worst-case scenario that could
possibly happen, returning to
camp and having to see what all
your tribe mates went through
the night before.
We tell each other over and
over, "When you win a reward,
don't feel guilty."
But, inevitably, you feel
guilty.
And it wiped everything out, you
know, including a good portion
of everybody's emotional steam.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe this.
I'm so sorry y'all had to go
through this.
It'll be all right.
How are you, Tina?
>> TINA: Did you have a good
time?
I know you were thinking about
us.
>> COLBY: I was.
>> TINA: I know you were.
>> COLBY: Oh, man.
Guys, I just... I can't believe
what happened.
When I walked up this morning...
>> RODGER: Sickening, wasn't it?
>> COLBY: ...it's sickening,
you're right.
Everyone's going through the
ringer right now.
And out of all six of us, I've
been the luckiest.
This immunity challenge is such
a double-edged sword for me.
I'm worried about saving my own
butt, but a bigger part of me is
worried about winning another
challenge and how that's going
to affect the way I'm viewed.
>> JEFF: You look worn out.
>> RODGER: We are.
>> JEFF: Quite a day yesterday.
>> AMBER: We'll be okay.
We've made it up until now.
We only have nine days left.
We're going to make it.
>> JEFF: Well, tonight we have a
tribal council.
I'll take back the immunity
talisman.
This is becoming very important
at this stage of the game.
Now, let's get to today's
immunity challenge.
You'll each have three plates
and a slingshot as a weapon.
For ammo, Australian macadamia
nuts.
Your goal: break the other tribe
member's plates before they
break yours.
When all your plates are broken,
you're out of the game.
The last person left standing
with a plate intact wins
immunity and you make the final
five.
Take your spot at a weapon.
Wait for my start.
Remember, you each have three
plates.
The last person with a plate
intact wins.
Survivors, ready... aim... fire.
>> COLBY: Ooh...! Hey.
>> KEITH: Sorry, bro.
>> COLBY: What's up with that?
>> KEITH: It's the pretty blue.
I love that color.
>> COLBY: You want to play like
that, huh?
>> JEFF: Aim... fire.
>> COLBY: Oh...
>> JEFF: First one down.
>> COLBY: The chef is cooked.
>> KEITH: Ouch.
>> COLBY: Ooh, that hurt.
>> JEFF: Aim... fire.
>> JEFF: Elisabeth and Amber.
>> RODGER: Sorry, Amber.
This is one straight away.
>> JEFF: Amber, Elisabeth, Keith
all have one plate out.
Aim... fire.
>> AMBER: Hey, buddy!
>> JEFF: Elisabeth, a gun-
slinger.
Amber, down to one plate.
Ready... aim... fire.
Tina.
>> COLBY: Sorry.
It was the closest one to me.
>> JEFF: Aim... fire.
>> KEITH: Sorry, bro.
>> COLBY: It's all right.
>> JEFF: Keith got even.
Rodger has no plates out.
>> RODGER: Shh. Shh, don't...
You don't have to tell them all
that.
>> JEFF: Aim... fire.
>> Oh!
>> JEFF: Boy, that meal did you
some good.
>> COLBY: Hey, I don't know what
it was.
>> JEFF: Eyesight is sharp.
Everybody has a plate out.
Amber has two.
Aim... fire.
Amber, you're out of the game.
Who took out Amber?
>> COLBY: I did.
It's nothing personal.
>> AMBER: I'm paying attention.
>> JEFF: Ready... aim... fire.
>> TINA: Whoo!
>> JEFF: Keith down to one
plate.
Rodger, you're down to one
Ready... aim... fire.
>> COLBY: Ooh.
>> Oh!
>> COLBY: Tina, wow.
>> RODGER: Sorry, sister.
>> KEITH: You get Colby over
there and I'll get Colby over
here.
>> KEITH: That's fine.
>> COLBY: Now, come on, guys.
>> JEFF: Ready... aim... fire.
Colby down to one plate.
Aim... fire.
Oh, Keith's out of the game.
Take a seat next to Amber.
Ready... aim... fire.
Tina, out of the game.
>> COLBY: See ya, Tina.
>> JEFF: Colby, you've taken a
lot of people out of this game.
>> TINA: What's wrong with this
picture, Colby?
>> COLBY: All the Ogakor.
What is wrong with this?
I'm jumping ship.
>> JEFF: Here we go, guys.
Ready... aim... fire.
>> COLBY: You're gone, Rodg.
>> JEFF: Rodger's out of the
game.
Here's where we're at.
Elisabeth, two plates perfectly
intact.
Colby down to one already
nicked.
Another winger will take it out.
>> AMBER: Elisabeth, you've got
a lot of pressure on you, girl.
>> Which one are you going for,
Elisabeth?
There's three plates up there.
>> JEFF: Ready... aim... fire.
Oh...
>> ELISABETH: Oh, boy.
>> JEFF: You're down to one
plate each.
Take your time and your shot.
This is for immunity.
Ready... aim... fire.
Elisabeth's out of the game.
Colby, this is becoming a
regular thing.
>> COLBY: Thank you.
>> JEFF: Congratulations.
Well, good luck with your camp.
You'll have fire after tonight's
tribal council.
Okay, guys, I'll see you
tonight.
>> KEITH: Going to tribal
council is not a fun thing.
I mean, you have no real good
reason for picking to vote
somebody off other than you're
trying to get to the end.
>> AMBER: It's sad to see
another person go out of your
group.
You know, it's less people, less
comfort, less conversations.
I never ever look forward to
going to tribal council, never.
I hate it.
>> ELISABETH: This group has
really endured a lot and
persevered through some really
torrential natural problems.
Tribal council becomes really
tough.
I think this is going to be one
of the toughest ones I've had to
go to.
>> JEFF: We out now bring in the
jury: Alicia, Jerry and Nick.
I'll just remind you, the jury's
not to be addressed.
They won't be addressing you,
just gathering information.
So when you last left here, I
said, "I wish for you dry
weather and no rain."
Obviously, my rain dance didn't
work out too well.
Rodger, there are two seasons in
the outback-- dry season, the
wet season.
This landscape has changed from
brown to green since we've been
here.
Yet you guys put your camp in
the mouth of a dry river bed.
Whose idea was it to put it
there?
>> RODGER: It was not my idea.
I was wanting to go up on the
hill and build.
But when the two tribes merged
at that time, we took a
consensus, and mostly the
females thought the sand would
sleep better.
I sure do wish we had went with
mine.
And then there was another
one or two that felt like we
should've went up on the hill,
too.
But we did all pull together
today.
I mean, everybody pitched in and
we're going to be all right.
>> JEFF: Elisabeth, how much
more difficult is this than what
you expected?
>> ELISABETH: I can say this:
every single day, especially
within the past four days, each
one has gotten exponentially
more challenging and difficult.
And I have gone from playing
this game challenge-to-challenge
to playing it day-to-day, and
now I just play it minute-to-
minute.
>> KEITH: After experiencing
what we experienced last night,
it's hard to put the game into
focus.
No one person could've stayed
warm by themselves last night.
It took every person together.
>> JEFF: Tina, you seem to be
playing the political game--
which it is still very
political-- but in as friendly
a manner as you can.
Was that a plan all along?
>> TINA: For me, that was
exactly my plan.
And I would rather spend the
last couple of weeks with people
who get along, are team players
and you know, want to see each
other do well.
And to me, that just means more.
>> JEFF: Let me follow that up,
then.
Is it fair to say that out of
the 16, the six most deserving
are still here?
>> TINA: Um... I don't know if I
could say that the six most
deserving, but I can say that
the six that are remaining
are... you know, these people
are all deserving, every one of
them.
>> JEFF: Well, you guys have
obviously bonded as Barramundi,
a new tribe.
But I'd be remiss if I didn't
point out the fact there's still
four Ogakor members and two
Kucha.
Rodger, you've been pretty
secure every time you've come to
tribal council.
Still feeling that secure
tonight?
>> RODGER: Oh, no.
The only way I would feel secure
is if I was wearing this
necklace that Colby's wearing.
And you never know what's going
to happen when you come here.
And I do think that eventually
the Kucha tribe will be an
extinct tribe, somewhere down
the line.
>> JEFF: Well, Colby's on a run,
that's for sure.
>> RODGER: He certainly is.
>> JEFF: You're the only person
who can't be voted for tonight,
yet you still get a vote.
Good place to be.
Let's vote.
Elisabeth, you're up.
>> ELISABETH: Amber, this is my
toughest vote yet.
It has to be done, nothing
personal.
>> RODGER: Really a sweet girl,
very tough decision for me to
make.
>> COLBY: Rodger, just sticking
with the batting order.
>> AMBER: Rodger, I just want to
thank you for all the comfort
that you've brought into camp.
It was like having a dad around.
I'm going to hate to see you go.
I'm going to miss you a lot.
>> KEITH: You're a really tough
competitor, and at this stage of
the game, you're hard to beat.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are tallied, the
decision is final.
The person voted out of the
tribe will be asked to leave the
tribal council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Rodger.
Amber.
Rodger.
Two votes Amber, two votes
Three votes Amber.
Last vote...
Amber.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> AMBER: I'll miss you guys.
Stay strong.
>> JEFF: Amber, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, based on tonight's vote, I
guess it's very clear the old
tribal lines of Kucha and Ogakor
are gone.
Take your new fire, head back to
camp and try to get a good
night's sleep.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode and hear
what Amber has to say.
Next time on Survivor...
A reward challenge brings
messages from home.
>> ELISABETH: I can't even
contain myself.
>> JEFF: Is that a little tear
in your eye?
"We miss you and we're very
proud of you."
But it's not one happy family
back at camp.
>> COLBY: Keith is cooking way
too much rice.
Said the brown rice yields less.
>> KEITH: No, I said you have to
use more water.
>> COLBY: The guy's a bozo.
My game with Keith is done, it's
over.
>> AMBER: I don't hold anything
against anybody.
You guys were the best five
people I could have spent my
last couple of nights with.
I'm actually kind of relieved.
Those last couple of nights were
really, really rough.
I'm very proud of myself to make
it this far, and I'm going to be
thinking about you guys a lot.
You're going to be in my prayers
and thoughts.
I will never, ever, ever, regret
anything that's happened here.