>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
The former Kucha tribe,
outnumbered by Ogakor's
alliance, fought to stay alive
by exploiting the tribe's
disdain for Jerri.
>> ELISABETH: I think there's a
crack in the tribe right now.
Jerri-- I think she's going to
get votes from their tribe.
>> JEFF: Jerri won the reward
challenge and chose Amber to
share in her victory, while back
at camp, Barramundi had their
own celebration without them.
>> KEITH: What's missing?
What's making it feel that way?
The Wicked Witch of the West
isn't here.
( Jerri laughing )
>> JEFF: Keith won immunity for
the second time in a row.
( thunder crashing )
The tribe hiked to tribal
council in a torrential
rainstorm...
Alicia.
...where the former Kucha
members learned that Ogakor's
alliance was still strong.
The tribe has spoken.
Alicia was voted out, becoming
the first member of the jury.
Eight are left.
Who will be the next to go?
>> COLBY: Last night it was just
tossing and turning all night.
The floor of the tent was
uncomfortable.
When the rain started coming in,
I was on the end, started
getting some water flow in my
side of the tent, just draining
off the tarp that we lay on.
And then wake up to see the rain
like this, our fire's out.
It's going to be a long day.
>> JERRI: Right now my main
concern is staying dry, 'cause I
don't want to get cold.
So I'm just feeling kind of
drained and lazy right now.
So... I'm sleeping in.
>> ELISABETH: It's a beautiful
day in the neighborhood.
>> RODGER: Yeah, maybe it'll
clear off.
Maybe it'll only rain half the
day.
>> AMBER: I hope our sunny days
aren't completely gone though.
>> ELISABETH: The rainy season
is upon us.
>> KEITH: They don't call me
fireman for nothing.
>> NICK: Look at that.
Look at that.
>> KEITH: The physical work is
not light.
You've got to go get wood,
you've got to break it down,
you've got to keep the fire
going.
And life in the outback is
tough, and it's getting tougher.
It really is getting tougher for
everybody.
( Nick gargling )
>> ELISABETH: What are you
doing, Nick?
>> NICK: I swear, every time I
swallow my throat just burns.
The roof of my mouth feels like
it's been burned for the last
three days.
>> ELISABETH: You have large
taste buds?
>> NICK: Enlarged.
>> ELISABETH: Wow.
>> NICK: I had in, like, three
or four enlarged taste buds on
my tongue, which just is
terrible.
And I'm feeling better, but my
mouth is still raw, so I can't
even drink water normally, and
it's just, like, ugh.
>> TINA: Sure doesn't look like
the spring water from home.
>> RODGER: No, that looks dirty.
>> NICK: That's 'cause the
river's so muddy.
If it's been boiled, then I'll
drink it.
We're out of water.
>> RODGER: We better... we need
to definitely boil up some
water.
>> NICK: Just dump it and get
some more.
>> RODGER: Yeah.
>> TINA: The rain settled in
here and it muddied our water,
and it's so cloudy, that fishing
has not been good at all.
We've lost all but two of our
hooks because we have to fish
from shore and there's a lot of
debris on the bottom.
>> RODGER: Tina, would you come
down here?
I'm going to have to get out of
the water.
I've got a line hung up.
>> TINA: You got a line stuck?
>> RODGER: Yeah, about two feet
offshore here.
The water's just so much
muddier.
Of course I'm taking a chance on
losing my hook in here, I do
know that.
Let me poke this way...
Maybe tomorrow, we got a full
day, maybe the water will clear
up a little bit...
>> TINA: Yeah.
>> RODGER: ...and try to get
some fishing.
Something besides rice.
>> COLBY: Because we're not
having the fish, we're having to
rely on our rice.
We're eating a lot more rice
than maybe we should be.
We're down to about two or three
days supply at the rate we're
going.
We still have eight people to
feed.
Keith, you want me to start the
rice in ten minutes?
>> KEITH: Yeah, if Jerri's up
for that.
>> AMBER: Or we could do the two
cups of rice, it doesn't matter.
>> ELISABETH: Maybe go back to
the two cups.
>> JERRI: One more meal of rice
is all we have left.
>> AMBER: At the most.
>> COLBY: Ooh.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh, I
knew it was going to be
something fun.
>> COLBY: A rope ladder.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh.
>> COLBY: Oh, my gosh.
Hey, guys, you guys are going
to dig this one.
>> ELISABETH: It's gonna be a
good one.
>> COLBY: They have upped the
ante.
It came on a rope ladder.
It says "Mental or physical, you
never can tell.
But you'll need a partner so,
you must pair up well.
One guy, one girl, one reward to
split.
If there's one reward to win,
then this one is it."
( exclaiming happily )
>> Wow!
>> COLBY: So we're splitting the
reward, and this one is going to
be big and chunky.
>> TINA: A good one.
>> ELISABETH: How do you guys
think we should decide partners?
>> AMBER: I don't know.
Should we pull them out of the
hat?
>> COLBY: You want to do that?
>> JERRI: I don't think so.
>> ELISABETH: You don't want to
pull out of a hat?
>> JERRI: No.
I think we should pick.
>> ELISABETH: Who would you
pick?
>> JERRI: I'd pick Colby.
>> TINA: Well, duh, who
wouldn't?
>> JERRI: Well, the whole thing
is, you know, when did this game
start being fair?
>> TINA: No, but I think it is
about team-manship.
>> RODGER: I'm the old guy here,
I know nobody wants to be with
me, but you know...
>> AMBER: Oh, Rodger!
>> RODGER: Sometimes you've just
got to go with the flow.
>> TINA: How we going to do it,
Colby?
>> COLBY: I've got all the
guys'
names written on a piece of
paper.
>> AMBER: And the girls pick?
>> COLBY: Yep.
>> AMBER: Don't open it yet,
till we all get one.
>> TINA: Did I get one?
>> COLBY: Yep, you got it.
Don't look at them yet.
All right, you can look at them.
>> AMBER: Keith, you're my
partner!
>> ELISABETH: Nick, you're my
partner.
>> JERRI: Colby.
>> TINA: Oh, my goodness.
>> ELISABETH: That's funny.
( scattered chuckling )
>> COLBY: Ready to rock?
>> JERRI: Yeah.
Ironically enough, I ended up
being Colby's partner, anyway.
I think it's important that
people are constantly reminded
of the reality of our situation.
There's nothing fair about this.
And... you know, it's about
winning.
>> COLBY: Jerri said, "Well, I
don't want to draw names."
Tina said, "Why not?"
She said, "I think we ought to
pick."
She said "Who would you pick?"
She said "Colby."
I'm sitting there going, well,
now hold on, let's think about
who Colby would pick here.
Granted, I want to win this
thing, but I don't know that I
want to share with her whatever
it is.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
Today's reward challenge
is the biggest one yet.
A helicopter is going to land at
Barramundi Beach and take you to
one of the Seven Wonders of the
World-- the Great Barrier Reef.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh.
>> JEFF: Where you'll go
snorkeling in the clear blue
water, and you'll be treated to
a great lunch.
The challenge is an obstacle
course.
You and your partner must stay
together.
There will be three heats with
two teams competing.
It's simple elimination.
If you win, you advance.
If you lose, you're out.
The winners from the first two
heats will move on to the final.
The winning team is going to the
Reef.
You've already drawn straws to
see who's going to race first.
You've picked your partners.
Let's go.
This is heat number one.
Winners move onto the final
round.
Survivors ready!
Go!
>> JEFF: Nice job, Keith and
Amber.
Take a break.
Heat number two, winners will
take on Amber and Keith in the
finals.
Survivors ready!
Go!
>> JEFF: Way to go, Colby and
Jerri.
Final heat, winners get a
private helicopter ride to the
Great Barrier Reef.
Here we go.
Survivors ready!
Go!
♪ ♪
>> AMBER: Are you okay, Keith?
>> KEITH: Just go...
>> JERRI: Come on, pull!
>> COLBY: Hold on.
>> JERRI: Ready?
( Colby grunting )
>> JERRI: Okay.
>> COLBY: Go.
>> JERRI: No! Colby!
( Jerri groans )
>> COLBY: Come on, come on, come
on.
Go, go, go, go.
Hurry up!
Go on, hurry up.
Hurry up, go.
( Jerri cries out )
>> JEFF: It's tight, it's tight.
>> COLBY: You got it.
Come on.
( Jerri yells )
You got it!
>> AMBER: Come on, Keith!
Come on!
( Jerri yells )
>> AMBER: Come on, Keith!
>> COLBY: That a girl.
>> JEFF: You guys are going to
the Great Barrier Reef.
>> AMBER: Are you packing all
your stuff?
>> JERRI: Yeah, I'm going to get
dressed, because we don't have
any idea what time.
>> KEITH: Colby left an hour
ago.
>> JERRI: He did not.
They wouldn't do that.
That would be so cruel.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah, that totally
would be cruel.
>> JERRI: You guys are funny.
>> KEITH: He tried to wake you,
and you said no, you didn't want
to go.
>> JERRI: I thought for sure
they'd be here by now.
>> AMBER: Me, too.
( engine whining )
>> TINA: Did y'all eat yet?
>> COLBY: Y'all could go ahead
and start.
>> TINA: Well, you may be hungry
before your trip.
You've got a long way to go.
>> AMBER: But the helicopter is
going to be here any minute.
( helicopter blades whirring )
( Rodger yawning )
>> JERRI: There's got to be a
little, little bit of animosity
and jealousy from everyone else
for winning two rewards in a
row.
It bothers me a little bit
'cause I can see where that
might affect people's voting.
But on the other hand, I really
couldn't give a flying crap, at
this point.
( laughing )
>> TINA: Your limousine.
>> RODGER: Y'all have... y'all
have fun.
Hope you... hope you get...
>> ELISABETH: We want details.
>> AMBER: Make sure you remember
everything you see.
>> JERRI: I will.
>> COLBY: I can't believe he
just landed on our beach right
there.
>> AMBER: I know.
>> ELISABETH: For you guys.
>> So which of you two are
coming for a fly with me today?
>> COLBY: We are.
>> Yeah, my name's Craig.
>> COLBY: Colby.
Nice to meet you, Craig.
>> CRAIG: Colby.
>> JERRI: Jerri.
>> CRAIG: Jerri, how are you
doing?
>> JERRI: Nice to meet you.
>> CRAIG: Let's head out to the
machine.
>> ELISABETH: Details, details.
Take note of everything.
>> NICK: I don't want details.
>> AMBER: This is something
they're going to remember for
the rest of their lives.
>> NICK: I'll remember this
thing today, too.
>> AMBER: Yeah, we will, too,
but...
>> NICK: Watching the helicopter
go away.
>> KEITH: Well, the kids are
gone for a day trip.
>> NICK: Let's eat.
>> AMBER: Let's eat!
>> ELISABETH: Let's eat.
>> CRAIG: We're getting over
level stuff now, we'll go down
and have a look at the trees,
and give you a bit of a close-up
look at the bush.
>> COLBY: All right!
>> JERRI: Yee-haw!
>> JERRI: We're in the middle of
nowhere.
>> CRAIG: Oh, yeah.
As we come up on the river
there, we're going to track
pretty much to the north, over
some rugged outback stuff, so
have a good look around where
you are.
>> COLBY: Sounds great.
>> COLBY: Oh, yeah!
>> JERRI: Whoo!
>> COLBY: I really got to get me
one of these choppers.
>> CRAIG: Nice waterfalls up
ahead.
>> JERRI: Wow!
>> CRAIG: Just a change of
scenery.
>> COLBY: Just think, Jerri, we
could be back on the beach
eating rice right now.
>> JERRI: It was meant to be,
Colby.
>> COLBY: I'm getting excited.
>> JERRI: We land on the beach
and I see a boat sitting there.
I'm, like, "What is going on?"
This is...
It couldn't possibly get any
better.
( whoops )
I don't even want to think about
anybody right now.
>> COLBY: No conversation about
strategy or Survivor today.
>> JERRI: I can handle that.
>> COLBY: I told Jerri as soon
as we got in the boat, I said,
"Here's the deal:
No talk about the game, no
strategy, no talk about the
other survivors.
Let's just enjoy the day for
what it is: a day off...
and that's it.
>> JERRI: Can't wait to get some
salt water in my hair.
>> COLBY: Can't wait to get some
food in my belly.
( laughing )
>> JERRI: Wow!
>> COLBY: Oh... no.
( Jerri gasps )
>> JERRI: Is that champagne?
>> COLBY: Looks like champagne
to me.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God!
>> COLBY: Bottled water.
>> COLBY: Underwater cameras.
Look at this.
>> JERRI: Unbelievable!
>> COLBY: Look at all this!
>> JERRI: We get under this tent
and there is just this spread.
There's a basket full of all
different kinds of fruits,
wrapped sandwiches, a bag of
Doritos... there's pasta salad
and sweet potatoes and all these
different vegetables.
>> COLBY: Look at this...
>> JERRI: A day at the beach!
>> COLBY: Look at what you get
here-- a little brownie.
>> JERRI: Oh!
>> COLBY: I know.
Gol-lee!
>> JERRI: Where do we start?
>> COLBY: Where do we start?
>> JERRI: Perfect.
>> COLBY: I feel rather spoiled
right now.
>> JERRI: We got champagne over
there.
>> COLBY: That'd be cool.
We don't need to have alcohol,
if we're going diving.
( Jerri laughs )
>> JERRI: Sure we do.
( cork pops )
We just... we feasted for
a good while, and then
realized, "I wonder how
everybody else is doing?"
But I knew.
>> AMBER: Around camp, we just
kind of did, you know, daily
chores and stuff.
Keith and I went and got some
firewood and broke some firewood
up.
Just normal taking care of our
camp stuff, you know, and not
too exciting, but just enough to
keep us busy to make the day go
by a little bit faster with
nothing to do.
Oh, no... he only said little
things-- I think he's just
really enjoying himself.
Just... you know...
Why not?
>> NICK: Just to get out of here
and see one of the wonders of
the world would have been great.
We're in the outback, but we're
seeing, you know, the same basic
spot over and over and over.
So to get out and see some
really clear blue water and have
a big meal, it would've been
great.
>> JERRI: Here we are in the
middle of the Great Barrier
Reef.
It was just too close to
paradise.
The setting-- it was very, very
romantic, on top of everything
else.
I even looked at him at one
point and I was, like, "This is
one hell of a first date,
Colby."
I couldn't have come out here
with a better person than Colby.
We're having a great time.
We're getting to know each other
outside of the game and outside
of that environment.
This is basically the perfect
honeymoon without the sex.
>> COLBY: Jerri was quite giddy
on our little getaway.
>> JERRI: Mmm!
>> COLBY: She made a comment to
me about it being a honeymoon
without the sex, and it couldn't
be farther from the truth for
me.
I mean, we certainly didn't sit
around and high five and say,
"Man, we finally get our time
alone together," you know?
That's not what I was looking
for.
I was just looking for some down
time away from the game and
that's what I got.
I do not want to leave here.
>> JERRI: I don't, either.
>> COLBY: It's hard back on
Barramundi Beach, being out
there 26 days going on a month,
and not have anything but rice,
so we're just going to go back
in and try to be as humble as
possible about it.
If somebody pisses me off, then
I'm going to just say, "I got to
go snorkeling on the Great
Barrier Reef.
What did you do today?"
>> JERRI: Returning to
Barramundi right now is...
I'm not really looking forward
to it.
But I at least am going back
feeling rejuvenated and renewed
and a little bit more like my
true self.
Because, man, after 26 days of
putting on the game face and
being this tough, you know,
"don't mess with me" chick--
but I got a tender side, too.
I feel like a little bit of that
was touched today.
>> KEITH: Well, let's see what
this noise is here.
That chopper is definitely
coming.
Yep, there it is.
Here they are.
>> ELISABETH: Where?
>> KEITH: Right coming over the
trees.
Right there.
>> ELISABETH: There they are.
>> Yeah.
We want details.
>> JERRI: That was awesome.
>> AMBER: Your meal?
What was your meal?
>> JERRI: Start out...
>> COLBY: Bananas, apples and
oranges.
>> Mmm.
>> JERRI: A couple of
nectarines.
>> COLBY: And a couple of
I wish everyone could have come
with us.
>> ELISABETH: Good jump start.
You got a jump start.
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> COLBY: But since you
couldn't, I brought a little bit
of the reef back to you.
( laughter )
Everybody gets their own piece
of coral.
>> Yay!
>> Oh!
>> AMBER: How exciting!
>> TINA: Wow.
That's very nice of you to do,
Colby.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh!
>> COLBY: This is Rodger's.
>> Oh...
>> RODGER: Thank you.
>> AMBER: Thank you so much!
>> ELISABETH: Thanks. It's...
>> COLBY: This one is Keith's,
and it has a little empty space,
kind of like the one between his
ears.
( laughter )
>> RODGER: There you go.
>> Oh.
>> COLBY: Here's your, uh,
orange for Tennessee.
>> RODGER: Oh, man.
>> TINA: Oh, Colby, thank you!
>> JERRI: Colby's little, um,
shell maneuver was most
definitely strategy.
For me, in a perfect world, it
would be me and him sitting up
there in front of the jury.
I find him and myself to be the
most even on the playing field,
more than anybody else here.
And so now, because of that
little maneuver, I'm thinking...
that he's got one up on me,
for sure.
>> Thank you.
>> ELISABETH: Colby, thank you
so much.
>> COLBY: You're welcome.
I wish y'all could have been
there.
>> TINA: That was so thoughtful.
>> AMBER: This is so cool!
>> It's so cool!
>> RODGER: Back there.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, wonder.
>> RODGER: That's exactly...
>> COLBY: That's one of the
seven wonders of the world.
>> RODGER: Yeah. Yeah. Ha.
>> NICK: Hey, Keith, can you
grab the funnel?
>> COLBY: Immunity is going to
determine who goes next time,
just like immunity determined
who... who's going tonight.
Nick comes over from Kucha, and
as Ogakor, we're still trying to
maintain some sort of control.
We determined a long time ago
that Nick was more of a threat
than say Elisabeth and Rodger.
So that determines why Nick goes
before them.
>> ELISABETH: Suckers.
>> RODGER: That's it.
( clattering in box )
>> NICK: Oh, I need some water.
>> RODGER: Grasshopper's in the
box!
>> KEITH: Nick's a strong guy,
although Nick's pretty much had
it.
He's-He's burned out, and he
says, "Listen, I'm rea...
You know, I'm ready to go."
So, I don't feel real bad about
that.
>> ELISABETH: I don't think
we've been alone together in a
long time, the three of us.
>> NICK: That's true.
>> RODGER: You're right.
>> ELISABETH: The remaining
Kucha survivors.
>> RODGER: This wind's blowing
right at ya.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah.
Well, basically, Kucha's
outnumbered right now by Ogakor,
and there's a chance, one by
one, we could go.
I know Nick feels as if he's
probably the next to go out of
our tribe, but if he wins
immunity, it could just as
easily be me or Rodger.
>> NICK: If I don't win the
immunity challenge, I think I'm
a goner.
I'll go boil water.
>> RODGER: Well, maybe that's
why.
They...
>> ELISABETH: We slave away in
the outback...
>> RODGER: They know...
They know...
>> ELISABETH: ...as our numbers
fall.
>> RODGER: They know that they
got us.
They know they got us.
>> NICK: Winning the immunity
challenge is important to stay
alive.
You know, you get out there, and
you try to compete and try to
win immunity challenges, but
looks like everybody is voting
on tribal lines at this point.
>> Wow.
>> AMBER: Oh, wow.
>> Oh!
>> JERRI: "Those with good
balance are in for a treat,
'cause now we find out..."
>> JERRI/ELISABETH: "...who's
sure on their feet."
>> JERRI: "If you keep steady
and don't rock the boat, you'll
head to the council, safe from
the votes."
>> KEITH: Today's the immunity
challenge.
It's an important day for
everybody.
The mail insinuated that we're
standing there on some kind of a
log structure, and I think it's
going to be in the water.
>> JEFF: I'll take this again.
>> KEITH: Yep.
>> JEFF: Mr. Consistency.
>> KEITH: From time to time.
>> JEFF: Put it back on its
perch.
Are you predicting another
victory today?
>> KEITH: Ah, I don't know.
>> JEFF: You're going to have to
share the wealth.
>> KEITH: Luck is on my side.
>> JEFF: All right.
Today's immunity challenge is
going to test your balance, not
your strength.
In fact, one of the keys is
figuring out how to use your
opponent's strength against them
to knock them off balance.
There will be three rounds.
Each round's a different
challenge.
It's single elimination.
Lose, you're out.
Win, you move on.
First round, you'll climb up
onto the towers, one against
another, and using a rope,
you're going to try and knock
your opponent off balance into
the water.
It's not a tug of war.
You can pull on the rope, or if
you want, just let it go.
Next round, you have a shaky
beam.
So, it's all about using your
legs and redistributing weight
to get them forward or
backwards.
>> AMBER: Wow.
>> JEFF: For the last round, the
finalists will square off on a
pair of unsteady platforms.
>> RODGER: Wow. Cool.
>> JEFF: As always, tribal
council tonight, immunity at
stake.
Certainly for one person.
Big, big stakes tonight.
Now, to be fair, you guys
have already randomly drawn
names to decide who will compete
against one another in the first
round.
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: All right.
Let's do it.
Keith, Rodger, you're up.
Survivors ready!
Go!
>> KEITH: I love ya, but you've
got to go.
>> Oh!
>> ELISABETH: Whoa.
>> KEITH: Dog you.
>> RODGER: Sneaky little
devil, ain't ya?
( laughter )
( screaming )
( applause and cheering )
>> RODGER: Yeah!
Whoo!
( mumbling )
>> JEFF: Rodger, moving on to...
( applause and cheering )
>> RODGER: Whoo!
>> JEFF: Nick, Jerri, grab your
rope.
>> JERRI: Do we have to put our
wrist in this thing?
>> JEFF: Yep.
>> COLBY: Put it around your
neck.
( Colby laughs )
>> JEFF: Survivors, ready.
Go!
>> RODGER: Oh.
Did you see his foot come up?
>> Oh!
( applause )
>> JEFF: Nick!
Moving on to round two.
Survivors ready.
>> TINA: Ready-o!
>> JEFF: Go!
>> TINA: Ah.
>> JERRI: Better be careful.
You know how he treats women.
>> TINA: Oh!
>> Oh!
>> AMBER: That was a quick one!
>> TINA: Ha-ha!
>> AMBER: Oh-ho.
That was quick.
>> JEFF: Colby's moving on.
>> ELISABETH: Colby, you're
cruel.
( Colby laughs )
>> JEFF: Survivors ready!
Go!
>> KEITH: Amber is an aggressive
little kitten.
( shrieking )
>> Oh.
>> JEFF: Amber, moving on!
>> JERRI: Good job.
>> JEFF: Okay, round two.
Once again, you've randomly
chosen the names of your
opponents.
Here we go.
Winner moves on to the finals
and a shot at immunity.
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> Oh, oh, get it, Rodg!
Get it, Rodg.
>> AMBER: Yeah, Rodger!
>> Come on, Rodg.
>> Go, Rodg.
>> Kick it, Rodg.
Kick it, Rodg.
>> Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
>> Oh!
( screaming )
( applause )
>> ...Rodg.
>> RODGER: Aah!
>> COLBY: Yeah, yeah!
>> JEFF: Colby, moving on!
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> ELISABETH: Whoo! Shake those
things.
They look like they're doing
some sort of strange dance.
>> Oh, oh.
>> NICK: I can't quite do that
like you can.
>> NICK: Oh. Oh, oh.
>> ALL: Whoa!
Oh!
>> Oh.
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: Nick, moving on to the
final round!
This is it!
For immunity.
The only thing that can
guarantee your security at
tonight's tribal council.
Survivors ready!
Go!
>> Oh.
>> KEITH: Ooh. Ooh!
>> NICK: Yeah, baby!
( applause and cheering )
>> JEFF: Nick wins immunity!
>> Oh, Nick!
>> Hey, Nick!
>> JEFF: Way to go, Nick.
Barramundi, see you tonight at
tribal council.
>> JERRI: Yeah!
>> RODGER: Good job, buddy!
>> ELISABETH: Yeah, yeah...
>> NICK: I hope I didn't seal
your fate.
>> ELISABETH: Hmm?
>> NICK: I hope I didn't seal
your fate.
>> ELISABETH: ...well, you
know...
>> RODGER: Could have been
either one of us here.
That's just...
>> NICK: Yeah.
>> RODGER: That's just the way
the old ball bounces.
>> ELISABETH: Uh-huh.
>> AMBER: It's weird, but I
think they all just know, so
they've come to accept it.
So, I think it's totally...
>> JERRI: The main thing that's
changing now that Nick has won
today's immunity is that we were
all going to vote him off
tonight.
So, it was discussed on the walk
back to camp who we would be
voting for instead.
It was decided by the ex-Ogakor
tribe that, um, Elisabeth would
be the next one to go.
>> ELISABETH: It made me scared
a little.
I was, like...
>> RODGER: Yeah, yeah.
Could be me or you.
>> ELISABETH: It could be.
>> AMBER: The tribal council's
definitely never a place where I
want to go.
I hate going every single time.
It's voting somebody off.
It doesn't matter if you've been
with that person the whole
entire time or only a couple
days.
It's still really hard to do.
I definitely want to talk to,
you know, Jerri and Colby and
Tina and Keith tonight to see if
our original plan's still in
effect.
The plan was kind of just get
rid of Kucha one by one by one.
>> ELISABETH: You guys are
pretty much in control-- you
know that-- 'cause of your
numbers.
And, I mean, I...
My next vote would be for Jerri,
anyway.
I think that she just brings
people down, and I don't like
how she is to even people on her
own tribe.
Her allegiance is only to
herself.
>> TINA: Mm-hmm.
But we have to vote you or
Rodger off.
>> ELISABETH: Mm-hmm.
>> TINA: Because, you know,
that's the safe thing to do.
>> ELISABETH: Right.
>> TINA: It's hard.
It's hard to talk about.
>> ELISABETH: Mm-hmm.
>> TINA: You know, because you
and Rodger just have more of
that heart and soul that we
want.
Me and Colby and Keith usually
get together and talk about the
order.
We all agree or disagree on
things.
>> COLBY: But there is one other
alternative.
That we can eliminate Jerri.
>> KEITH: I mean... we are...
We're stuck with her...
Well...
I don't know.
>> COLBY: Keith, I'm sorry, but
we're talking about a lot of
money at stake.
>> KEITH: No, I understand that.
I understand that, man.
>> COLBY: Okay.
>> KEITH: We have an opportunity
that is staring us right in the
face, and it's guaranteed.
Want to get rid of Jerri
collectively?
>> COLBY: Keith, listen to what
you just said.
Why would we allow that
possibility to even come to
fruition when we've got an
opportunity right now to keep
things going exactly the way
they are, and then get rid of
Jerri as soon as we can?
And, boy, do I want to.
Man, I had to put up with her
all day yesterday.
>> KEITH: You know, it's, uh...
>> COLBY: I can't imagine
getting rid of Elisabeth over
her, but...
>> KEITH: I know, and, uh...
>> COLBY: It's just...
It's-It's...
>> KEITH: My gut tells me...
>> COLBY: It's the right move.
>> KEITH: I understand.
I mean, it makes sense.
>> COLBY: Blue.
>> JERRI: Hey.
>> RODGER: Hey, now.
Here you go.
>> JERRI: We're off like a herd
of turtles.
( indistinct conversation )
>> JEFF: Now, I'll bring in the
first member of our jury.
The jury is not to be addressed.
No comments, reference to the
jury.
The jury will not speak to you.
The jury is merely here to
gather information that they
will use in deciding which one
of the final two gets the
million dollars.
Each tribal council, as you guys
are voted off, you will become a
part of the jury, and the power
will shift to that side.
Nick, on a scale of one to ten,
how important was immunity for
you today?
>> NICK: Oh, this is a ten.
If, um... if I hadn't won
immunity today, I fully expected
to get voted off.
>> JEFF: Based on?
>> NICK: Based on the way voting
has been going, uh, based on
my place in the tribe.
Uh, I-I fully expected if I lost
today to, uh, be sitting on...
in the jury the next... next
time around, so...
>> JEFF: Jerri, as you look at
the jury, you got one member
over there.
You guys, right now, have a one-
in-eight shot at a million
bucks.
Have you surprised yourself with
the way you've acted out here?
>> JERRI: Honestly, I had no
idea that this was going to be
as tough as it is.
And I have woken up in the
morning and gone through an
entire day wondering who I am.
Things come out of my mouth in
frustration and out of hunger
and just stress that, after they
come out, I want to suck them
back in and... 'cause I...
It's not something that I would
normally say or... or act.
So, yeah, I've surprised myself
in a lot of ways.
>> JEFF: Elisabeth, due to the
numbers, you're having to sort
of go their way.
Worried at all?
Strong competitor, you're going
to be tough if you get to the
final two.
You're probably a target at some
point.
>> ELISABETH: That definitely
goes through my mind.
You know, you come here, and
basically, anyone is a target.
But when you're in a minority,
you know, of numbers, the
reality sets in a little more
harshly.
You're always vulnerable here.
Nothing is guaranteed, and you
can't assume anything, because
that's the most dangerous,
dangerous thing you can possibly
do here in the outback in this
game is assume.
Assume you're safe,
assume you're right.
You're not.
And, so I come here prepared...
for the worst.
>> JEFF: So, let's vote.
Elisabeth, you're first.
>> AMBER: Elisabeth, this is
going to be the hardest vote
yet, and the hardest vote for
the rest of the game.
But the only reason why I am
making it is because I made a
word with my original tribe, and
I want to stick to my word.
>> RODGER: Most days, she gets
up in a good mood, but oh, baby,
look out if she gets up in a bad
mood.
>> JERRI: I've never in my life
met anyone more likable and more
lovable.
Because you are such a likable
person, it is a definite threat.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are tallied,
the decision is final.
The person voted out of the
tribe will be asked to leave the
tribal council area immediately.
First vote...
Elisabeth.
Jerri.
Two votes Elisabeth, two votes
Three votes Jerri.
Four votes Jerri, two votes
Elisabeth.
Five votes Jerri.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> JERRI: Checkmate.
You guys got me.
( laughs )
Good game.
>> JEFF: Jerri, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Based on that vote, maybe the
game has changed, and a new
tribe finally has been born.
Barramundi is alive and kicking.
You guys can head back to camp.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode and hear
what Jerri has to say.
Next time on Survivor:
The tribe wakes up and realizes
that Jerri is really gone.
>> COLBY: Sweet.
>> ELISABETH: Her own tribe
voted against her.
>> JEFF: But the survivors are
too hungry to celebrate.
>> ELISABETH: I'm just, like,
shaking and weak.
>> JEFF: They are offered more
food, but at what price?
>> JERRI: You know, it's funny
because I absolutely knew this
was coming.
It must have been my remark
about how this game isn't fair.
I'm pretty sure that's what set
everyone off.
I've had a great time.
And I'm still up for sitting
around with everybody having a
beer and laughing about this
whole thing.