>> JEFF: We're onboard a 38-
squadron Caribou DHC-4 military
aircraft on loan from the Royal
Australian Air Force.
Normally, these planes are used
to rescue people in dangerous,
life threatening situations.
Today, however, we have a
different mission.
These 16 Americans are about to
be abandoned.
This plane will land in the
heart of one of the most
unforgiving places anywhere on
earth: the Australian outback.
For the next 42 days, they'll be
left to fend for themselves,
forced to work together to
create a new society while
battling the elements and each
other.
They must learn to adapt, or
they'll be voted from the tribe.
In the end, one will remain and
will claim the million-dollar
prize.
42 days, 16 people, one
survivor.
( retching )
As this plane touches down on a
remote strip of land in the
Australian outback, these 16
strangers begin the adventure of
a lifetime.
They have never spoken to each
other, and the rules state they
must remain quiet until after
the plane has landed, dropped
them off, and abandoned them.
They have been separated into
two competing tribes: Kucha and
Ogakor.
One crate of supplies awaits
each tribe, and once the plane
has taken off, they will have
only five minutes to salvage
whatever they can carry.
They then face a grueling 5-mile
hike that will take them deep
into the outback and their new
homes for the next 42 days.
The Kucha tribe, which will
always wear blue, consists of
Kimmi Kappenberg, a bartender
from Long Island; Michael
Skupin, a father and software
publisher and distributor from
White Lake, Michigan; Alicia
Calaway, a personal trainer from
New York City; Rodger Bingham, a
farmer and school teacher from
Crittenden, Kentucky; Elisabeth
Filarsky, a footwear designer
from Newton, Massachusetts; Nick
Brown, a Harvard law student
from San Francisco; Debb Eaton,
a corrections officer from
Berlin, New Hampshire; and Jeff
Varner, an Internet projects
manager from Greensboro, North
Carolina.
>> JEFF V.: Whoo!
So cold.
>> JEFF: Ogakor tribe, which
will always wear green, consists
of Maralyn Hershey, a retired
police officer from Wakefield,
Virginia; Colby Donaldson, an
auto customizer from Christoval,
Texas; Amber Brkich, an
administrative assistant from
Beaver, Pennsylvania; Mitchell
Olson, a singer-songwriter from
Vermillion, South Dakota; Tina
Wesson, a mother and personal
nurse from Knoxville, Tennessee;
Keith Famie, a chef from West
Bloomfield, Michigan; Jerri
Manthey, an aspiring actress
from Los Angeles, and Kel
Gleason, an Army intelligence
officer from Fort Hood, Texas.
( cheering )
>> NICK: Wait, guys, there's got
a be a way to prop it open, I
think.
>> AMBER: "Welcome to the
Australian Outback.
As of right now, you are
"completely cut off from the
outside world."
>> ALICIA: "These are the only
supplies you'll be given.
Choose wisely, since you still
"have a long way to carry them.
Fresh water is essential to your
survival.
"Unfortunately, all of the water
you will need for the next few
days must be taken from your box
"because the river water must be
boiled, and you may not be able
to make a fire."
>> DEBB: We're Kucha?
>> Kucha?
>> AMBER: Ogakor.
>> MARALYN: Ogre Kor.
>> TINA: We have the map.
>> NICK: Start... I guess we're
starting here.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah.
>> NICK: Okay, that's north.
>> How much do you need?
>> DEBB: I don't know the names
yet.
In the green hat right here.
Can you help her get one side of
this undone?
>> MARALYN: Can we pee soon?
>> Take every, every everything.
>> MICHAEL: Come on, guys, we
need to go now.
>> Grab something, all right?
>> All right, we'll get it,
we'll get it.
>> JEFF: The tribes will split
up and head in opposite
directions.
Their camps are situated four
miles apart, along the shore of
the Herbert River.
Each beach has a flag and a
canoe.
Finding these sites will be the
first unofficial challenge for
the new survivors.
>> KIMMI: Whoever's got the
compass...
Okay, northeast we have to go?
>> NICK: It seems like it's not,
but, okay...
>> KIMMI: That's north.
>> NICK: That's north right now,
so northeast is, like, across
back that way.
>> KIMMI: That way.
We're going the wrong way.
>> ALICIA: When they dropped us
off, you know, everybody was
designated a certain thing to
do, and, uh, they gave Nick the
compass.
For some reason, although the
compass said one way... we kept
going the wrong way.
>> DEBB: Tell me something.
He's telling me we're moving
this way.
>> ALICIA: I know we are.
Yankees?
>> DEBB: Are we moving in the
right direction?
>> ALICIA: Absolutely, all the
way, baby.
>> I think we should check, like
every...
>> DEBB: All right, then that's
where we're going. Nick? Nick?
Stay in the front, Nick, and
keep us going north to
northeast, okay, but keep us
going north...
>> MICHAEL: There's a... there's
a beaten path.
>> KIMMI: What's your name
again?
>> MICHAEL: Mike.
>> ALICIA: Mike.
>> DEBB: Let's just stop for one
second and look at the map.
>> MICHAEL: All right.
>> DEBB: And look at the
compass.
>> MICHAEL: All right.
>> DEBB: Just to make sure,
'cause it's a long ways to where
we're going.
>> NICK: Even from the
beginning, I was finding, like,
people were automatically
getting on people's nerves.
Um, yeah, we were walking
through the grass, and Kimmi was
like, "I can't stand, uh, Debb."
>> DEBB: See, if we're going
southwest, how are we going to
hit the dry creek bed?
>> KIMMI: Because that's north!
>> DEBB: That's right, so we're
not going to hit it unless we go
that way.
>> KIMMI: Debb's not even a bad
person.
She means well.
It's just she's not somebody
that in the outside world that I
would talk to, because... she'd
make me crazy.
>> MARALYN: When you traverse
something that I could bust my
butt on, let me know.
The hike, uh... it was a little
intimidating.
Um, I was afraid.
"Good grief, what if I get so
winded that I can't keep up?"
Do you see the flag?
Wait a minute, hang on.
>> COLBY: You all right,
Maralyn?
That trek let me know that this
was for real.
That was a long trek we had
through deep sand with a lot of
heavy equipment, and I was
packing more weight than anyone
else, so I was really
struggling.
It was a long trip, and that
was... that fired me up, because
that is the quickest way to find
out what people are made of.
>> AMBER: ( groans )
I'm a little tired.
This rice is very heavy.
I really want to get there soon.
>> COLBY: We don't know how far
away we are, so I'm going to run
up this and do a little
reconnaissance, see if we can't
find out where we're at.
I figure if it's really far,
we'll drape some of our stuff
here, and we won't take it.
If we're not far, then we'll
buck up and get it there.
Yeah, I'm going to keep going.
We're just going to follow the
creek bed here, and, uh, make
sure if it looks like it's
getting too dark, you turn back
and come get us.
>> JERRI: Keith actually ran
ahead to go scout out where the
camp was, 'cause we were all
getting pretty tired, and the
last leg of that walk was really
difficult.
>> COLBY: I wish the snakes
would...
>> MARALYN: Never let 'em see
you sweat.
>> KEL: Keith?
>> KEITH: Here I come.
>> KEL: Okay, what do you see?
>> KEITH: I found it.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Yay!
>> Let's go!
>> JERRI: Whoo!
( laughing )
>> Whoo!
>> JERRI: Whoo!
>> Yeah!
( cheering )
( grunts )
>> JEFF V.: I'm feeling really
weak, and, um, on the verge of
throwing up just ever since I
got here.
I mean, it started with the
plane flight.
In the beginning, it was really
fun, and it was kind of cool and
groovy, and I was enjoying the
ride, and then all of a sudden,
I just got sort of nauseous, and
I kept thinking to myself, 'I'm
not going to get sick.
'I'm not going to get sick.
I will not throw up.'
So I sort of went into this
little zone and breathed, and I
don't remember any of it.
>> KIMMI: Rodger carried one of
the big water jugs.
Mike had a big water jug.
Poor Elisabeth had the board on
her head, and then I had the
eight bottled waters wrapped
around me, so the-the four of
us kind of got separated from
the other four when we were
walking to our campground.
>> ELISABETH: I mean, everything
was heavy to carry.
You can't discount any of our
equipment as easy to carry, but
some of it was just more
awkward.
And some of the crossings, we
had to go, you know, down a
sharp valley of rocks. and up
again, and kind of wind and
balance across a river.
And it was frustrating, too, but
with the water jugs and, you
know, the water canteens, and...
I mean, that stuff is just
awkward.
>> Oh, I see the flag.
Oh, my God!
Welcome to our home.
>> Right up there.
>> KIMMI: When we arrived, it
was just a moment of ecstasy,
'cause it's like, "Yes!
I've worked this far just to see
this silly thing."
I mean... And not just
physically from here, but just
mentally preparing yourself the
whole journey, like, all the
airplane flights from New York
to California to Australia, from
the other part of Australia to
here to there.
You know, there were just so
many things in sequence to get
you to that flag that just being
at that flag is just an
accomplishment.
( yelling )
( cheering )
( thunder rumbling )
>> DEBB: We should be up-up in
the trees to some degree.
There's no shelter here at all.
>> ELISABETH: As soon as we got
out of the river, I think we
just... this kind of
realization.
We got a little cold, and we
realized that we're going to...
we have to sleep somewhere, and
we just wanted to feel a little
safe and dry.
So we got to work as much as we
could on building the basis of a
home.
>> DEBB: We got enough rocks
here, too!
We could build a pretty decent
shelter just using rocks!
>> MICHAEL: ( groans )
It's going to make is softer to
sleep on.
>> ALICIA: Want to see a what?
>> DEBB: That means there's
snakes in there.
>> MICHAEL: When we started
building the shelter, I thought
everybody started chipping in,
because there was the wood
gatherers, and there was the
people that were building, and,
uh, I had worked a lot of, uh,
you know, some construction in
my life, and I-I had a
reasonable sense of, uh, of-of
construction.
What we're going to have to do
is just cut little holes in
here, and then just tie it
around the top here about this
high, so that we can just make
it right here.
Um, we need one to go right
about halfway up along this
support right here.
>> DEBB: It seems like one
individual in the group is...
ordering everybody around, and
if you guys haven't figured it
out, it's Mike.
>> MICHAEL: Rodger, get the
level out and see how we're
doing.
>> ELISABETH: Okay.
>> DEBB: You can't have one
person step in and start
ordering everybody around,
'cause it's not going to play,
and it's not playing right now,
and not just with me, but with
others.
>> MICHAEL: Here. Push up.
Push that up a little bit,
Rodger, so I can give me a
little...
Push this up a little bit.
>> DEBB: Rodger used to build
homes.
Rodger is the one who helped to
build this shelter.
He knows what he's doing.
Well, Mike comes over and starts
telling him how to build it,
and-and Rodger was like, "No,
that isn't going to work."
>> RODGER: It's going to give us
fall this way plus both
directions.
>> MICHAEL: I mean, do you think
it's enough of a pitch here
to... so the rain's going to
come off good?
( grunts )
We're never going to want to
leave this place.
>> RODGER: I don't know about
that.
>> Very quickly.
>> Yeah, we're doing really
well.
>> KEITH: All right, so, what
makes the most sense as far as
building where we'd want to
live?
Do we want to live by the water,
or do we want to take a walk up
on the high ground and take a
look at it?
>> MARALYN: Well, there's a lot
of electrical storms.
>> Yeah, good point.
>> There's going to be a lot of
bugs down by the water, though.
>> JERRI: We want to definitely
be under some trees, 'cause, I
mean...
>> Okay.
>> JERRI: When the sun comes
out, it's going to be hot.
>> MARALYN: Probably the sun is
going to be out at certain
times, so at certain times,
there's still going to be shade,
based on the position of the
sun.
>> Do you have a compass with
you?
>> KEITH: As soon as we hit the
beach, and it was really kind of
amazing, collectively, we all
dispersed to do something
different.
>> JERRI: When we got to our
camp, I was considering at that
point anything and everything
anybody was doing or saying as a
strategic move.
>> MITCHELL: Colby-- his luxury
item was the Texan flag, which
was great, because it served as
the tarp that covers... covers
us and blocks us from the wind
and the sun.
>> COLBY: I really did bring the
flag to serve as shelter, but,
you know, don't get me wrong.
When I wake up in the morning,
there's two things I'm thankful
for: I'm thankful I'm alive, and
I'm thankful I'm a Texan.
>> It's not going to work.
>> JERRI: We don't need to risk
ripping this if there's a stick
that's two inches shorter.
>> KEITH: Yeah, you don't need
to go that far, though.
>> JERRI: It was...
No, but it's not going to stay.
That's what I'm saying.
The tension between Keith and
I...
I think him and I kind of...
rubbed each other the wrong way.
>> KEITH: Watch, right here,
watch.
Let me just show you.
Right there.
>> KEL: It's sticking now.
>> KEITH: It's set. It's-it's...
That's-that's working.
And before it was here.
>> JERRI: But, see, we put it on
the grommet for a reason: so
that the flag wouldn't rip.
>> KEITH: You can't.
You won't be able to go through
that on a flat surface.
>> JERRI: Keith and I didn't
start off on a very good foot,
just because of some of the
condescending mark... remarks he
made to me, and he might very
well not even be aware that he
does it, but I'm not the kind of
person to just let it slide off
my back.
All right, all right.
>> You got to share something
about yourself that's really
embarrassing.
>> Okay.
>> Embarrassing or just deep?
>> KIMMI: I just got naked in a
tent with a bunch of strangers.
>> RODGER: That's what I was
getting ready to say.
>> ALICIA: Give us the dirt,
girl.
>> Like boyfriend, husband,
wife.
>> KIMMI: Okay, A, not married.
Don't believe in marriage until
I'm 35.
>> Okay, don't say you're a
virgin, 'cause I swear to God,
I'll...
( laughter )
>> KIMMI: I'll tell you what my
main concern was: when and how
am I going to masturbate out
here with...
( laughter )
>> You have got to be kidding
me!
>> DEBB: Kimmi is a happy-go-
lucky person who's got...
I-I don't even know how to
describe her.
I don't know what the right word
is.
You know, nothing is taboo with
her-- nothing at all.
>> KIMMI: Listen to me!
You guys might like a skin wig,
however... on occasion.
>> JEFF V.: Kimmi will not shut
up.
You know, I'm tired at night.
I want to go to sleep, and
they're constantly talking, and
with the headache that I have,
it just reverberates.
Kimmi cannot say a single thing
without screaming it.
>> KIMMI: All right, someone
just stuck their finger in my
...!
>> DEBB: Well, it was on my
head.
>> JEFF: All of a sudden, out of
the blue, with that accent that
just talks and talks and talks
and talks...
I just want to grab her by the
neck and shake the ... out of
her, you know?
>> KIMMI: Oh, my God, I love
you!
I can take my braids out!
And you had a threesome.
We went back-to-back.
You farted in my ... and
rebounded it...
>> MICHAEL: I think we're
starting to get to know each
other, and people are not
accustomed to this kind of
lifestyle yet.
I'm a little accustomed to this
lifestyle, because I do hunt,
and I do fish, and I do camp, so
it's not that foreign to me.
Kucha, we got food!
>> Oh, my God.
>> Right, like, right under our
noses.
>> Is it better?
>> MICHAEL: Yeah, I think you
can eat 'em.
When I saw those figs, it was a
big rush, and two or three
people came over and helped pick
the figs, and we brought 'em
back, and, uh... I bit into one
right off the tree.
( yelling )
( spitting )
Don't!
>> What? What? What?
>> MICHAEL: ( spitting )
Don't bite into one.
>> Dang fruit flies.
>> I know.
Well, we're going to put the...
>> Can we eat 'em green?
>> Look at that.
>> That's not bugs, is it?
>> No, that's not bugs.
If they're not...
if they're not moving.
>> JEFF V.: I'm looking at bugs.
>> DEBB: All over the place here
with this.
>> JEFF V.: Let's see.
Mike, he opens up these figs,
and he's... showing us these
bugs, and I'm just wanting to
eat that thing so bad, 'cause
I'm starving, and these bugs are
just creepy and flying around,
and I don't eat anyth...
You know, I-I cook my food.
>> ALICIA: And if the bugs don't
fly out, I'm going to eat them,
so...
>> JEFF V.: Speak for yourself,
baby.
>> DEBB: We very well might be
cold and hungry tonight, but not
if we can help it.
The fire is the most important
thing for survival.
We need to eat, and we need to
boil water.
That's all I care about.
If we put enough sand in there,
I think it's good.
Put that cotton right at the
bottom.
>> MICHAEL: Well, the problem is
we get too much sand in here,
we're not... we're... it's
dumping on all of our tinder.
This wood's not going to catch
fire.
The tinder's going to catch
>> DEBB: Just... you need to
keep that...
>> MICHAEL: But if you keep
putting sand in there, it-it
puts out the tinder.
>> DEBB: I know. It's just that
the book said you needed
friction.
>> KIMMI: Debb works very hard,
and she means well, but she's
like, "Well, in the camping
book, it says to do it like
this."
And-and you know what?
We could have the wrong wood.
We could have the wrong rocks,
something.
She's making herself an
authority on something actively
on what she read and not on
actually doing.
Had she went and practiced this
stuff at home, I would take her
opinion a lot more, you know,
seriously.
>> All right.
>> RODGER: One thing we tried to
do in starting the fire was use
my Bible, which I had brought
along.
It was my luxury item.
And, uh, we tore some pages out
of it.
Uh, it wasn't the pages that
actually had any scripture in
it, but I would've used that.
You know, if you're...
You got to do with what you got.
>> Next?
>> I don't know.
I don't...
>> RODGER: Yeah.
There's a letter from my son-in-
law he wrote me.
>> Oh.
>> RODGER: Read it.
I don't have my glasses.
>> KIMMI: Do you want me to read
it to you out loud...
>> RODGER: I don't care.
I can't; I don't have my
glasses.
>> KIMMI: "Dear Dad, best of
luck.
"You have many people who
believe you can do anything you
"put your mind to.
Just be yourself.
"Things'll be fine in Kentucky.
Focus on your task at hand.
"You can do this.
It's not going to be easy, but
"a challenge such as this
shouldn't be easy.
Just try your best."
>> All right.
>> KIMMI: It says "KJA", and
then he put in parentheses
"141", so I don't know if
that...
>> RODGER: 141? Yeah.
>> KIMMI: Oh!
>> That's pretty cool.
>> KIMMI: You got love notes.
>> RODGER: That was a nice
little piece of home when you...
when you least-least expect it,
you know.
Then it said go to page 200, and
then go to page 150, and we went
through that about seven or
eight times, I think, till we...
till we finally came to the end.
>> KIMMI: Can you give us the
page of the burning bush?
>> RODGER: And it was a little
sentimental for me, to tell you
the truth, to... to hear it.
>> I think you wrote the book,
huh?
>> KEITH: My son is in Cub
Scouts.
If I start this fire, I will be
his hero.
( laughter )
>> COLBY: Ooh, this side got
hot.
>> JERRI: Are we far enough
away from the water?
>> MITCHELL: Just what I was
going to say right there.
>> KEITH: Oh, it doesn't...
I think we start the fire, we
can dig anywhere we want to.
We pull off making the fire...
>> JERRI: Well, I don't even
really want to attempt to start
it until we get it where we want
to keep it.
>> Yeah.
>> JERRI: 'Cause if we move it,
it's going out.
>> KEITH: Well, let me keep
trying on this.
>> JERRI: If you get lucky, and
you spark that thing, and it's
ready to go, and you try and
pick it up and move it, and we
don't have anywhere to put it,
then...
>> KEITH: Then I can just keep
it burning here and a little one
going, and we can always move
this.
>> JERRI: All right, I'm going
to go see if I can find a better
place.
>> MITCHELL: Bad news.
>> KEITH: I've never started a
fire before from scratch, but,
you know, I knew nightfall was
coming.
We'd have no light, and we'd be
able to cook nothing, um... and
we wouldn't have a bonfire, so
it was... it was pretty
critical.
>> COLBY: Keith is just licking
his chops.
He's wanting to cook so bad, he
can't stand it, and so you can
bet he's going to work on this
fire thing until we lick it.
>> AMBER: Uh-oh.
>> KEITH: Oh.
Since Jerri and I had our little
confrontation before, I thought,
you know, this is a great time
to get her involved with this
process, to be a part of it
somehow, with something she
brought that was important to
her.
>> JERRI: Fire.
Ah!
>> KEITH: ( indistinguishable )
>> JERRI: Whoo!
>> KEITH: I can feel it.
Oh, my God!
( screams )
>> KEITH: Oh, my God!
>> JERRI: Wow.
Are you guys okay?
>> MARALYN: Until we can get a
fire and boil water... we're not
going to be eating much of
anything.
>> KIMMI: I got the mail...
>> No way!
( cheering )
>> DEBB: All right! Read it.
Read it to me.
>> Oh, my God.
>> All right, what does it say?
>> KIMMI: "You expected dry
weather, but then you slept in
the rain, and you can't get a
"spark no matter how hard you
strain.
To get your tribe's fire, pay
"heed to this note: the winners
take matches, the losers cast
first the vote."
>> Oh!
>> DEBB: Yeah!
>> ELISABETH: We are getting
matches!
>> When, though? When?
>> We are definitely...
>> Matches!
>> KIMMI: All right, we just got
our notice for the first
immunity challenge, and we're
going to go kick some butt,
'cause we're all together on
this, and we're going to go get
us some fire, and we're going to
go, uh, get us some food.
Fire means food, so that's what
we're going to go do.
We're going to go there, we're
going to fight hard and win.
>> ELISABETH: Winning immunity
is the most important thing.
We need to... beat, beat, beat
the other tribe.
We'll let them eliminate someone
on their team first.
>> MITCHELL: This immunity
challenge is extremely
important, because we have to
show the other team that we're
better, you know, and plus, we
have to have fire in order to
start eating rice.
>> JEFF: What's up, guys?
Gather up.
So, uh, anybody have any luck
with fire?
>> ALICIA: No luck.
We came close.
>> Almost.
>> MICHAEL: We got a lot of
smoke.
>> JEFF: All right, I got
something that's going to help
the smoke.
Waterproof matches.
One of the things we're playing
for tonight, right here, a
little canister full.
We're also playing for something
else much more important than
waterproof matches.
Right here: the immunity idol.
You want to know this guy really
well, because the tribe that
wins the immunity idol will not
have to go to Tribal Council and
vote out one of their own
members.
That brings us to challenge
number one.
You're playing for fire.
You're playing for immunity.
There are four legs in the race.
You'll be carrying a lit torch.
If somebody falls in the water
at any time and their torch goes
out, your tribe is done.
Somebody's going home tomorrow.
So that is key.
Here's how the game is played.
First leg starts at the old
bridge.
You'll make your way across
using two planks to help you
bridge the gaps.
On the second leg, you'll cross
over the island, where you'll
find, in the water, a small
torch-carrying raft.
Put your lighted torch on the
raft and, as a tribe, swim
across to the other side of the
bank.
When you get over there, you'll
find two sets of wooden rungs.
Take them with you.
For the third leg, you're going
to get on another raft, and
using a rope, pull yourself
across the river.
Using the rungs, climb up the
ladder, light the torch.
Winners: maybe a hot meal
tonight, security of knowing
you're going to be here a while.
Losers: cold, somebody's going
to be the first person voted out
of the tribe.
Make sense?
Let's take our spots, wait for
my start. Let's go.
All right, at stake, fire... and
immunity!
Survivors, ready?!
>> Ready!
>> JEFF: Go!
>> We won, we won, we won!
Continue to move forward!
Move it forward! Move it
forward!
Go, go, go!
>> This is a team.
This is a team.
>> Go, go, go, go, let's go.
We got it.
>> NICK: Go, go.
Help her a little. Help.
Go, go, go.
>> We're even. Go, guys, run.
Go, go, go, go.
>> Get the fire.
Hand on the raft.
>> Let's go.
>> Come on, come on!
>> ALICIA: Let's go, let's go.
>> Put your hand on the raft,
Kel.
>> RODGER: Okay, I'm okay. Go.
>> DEBB: Wait.
>> Wait, his foot's caught.
Oh, my God.
>> Watch your step, watch your
step!
>> ALICIA: We're almost there.
>> Work, work, work.
>> JERRI: Whoo! Yeah!
( cheering )
>> Mitchell.
>> Go.
>> Back up, back up.
>> Whoo!
>> JERRI: Mitchell!
>> We got it.
Don't lean too far right.
>> Good job! You got it!
>> Mitchell!
( cheering )
Damn, we're good.
>> My God!
>> JEFF: Ogakor,
congratulations.
>> TINA: Whoo!
>> JEFF: Nice work.
>> COLBY: Ow!
>> JEFF: Guys, your reward,
right here: waterproof matches.
>> JERRI: Yeah!
>> AMBER: Yeah!
>> JEFF: And much more
important, I think, you're in
possession...
>> AMBER: Wow...
>> JEFF: ...of the immunity
idol.
( cheering )
>> We need to stay positive now,
okay?
>> JEFF: Guys, tomorrow,
somebody from Kucha will be the
first person voted out of the
tribe.
You'll have that to think about
tonight.
I know you're already a close
group.
It's going to be a tough
decision.
You guys can head on back to
camp.
Ogakor, you guys can light this
up in celebration.
>> RODGER: Yesterday's immunity
challenge was a big letdown, uh,
uh, not only physically, but
emotionally.
I think probably more so
As far as the Tribal Council
goes tonight, which are... which
we have to go to, uh, I don't
think any of us are looking
forward to it.
( gagging )
( retching )
>> Jeff is not well.
>> ELISABETH: You need to sit
down.
You're so shaky, you're scaring
me.
>> JEFF V.: That's okay.
>> DEBB: I don't know.
I'm not betting on me getting
voted off, but I think it's-it's
down to, like, me, Rodger or
maybe, um... Jeff, because he
hasn't been feeling good.
My personal opinion is the
strong survive.
If you were going to vote for
someone, who would you be voting
for right now?
>> RODGER: Jeff.
>> DEBB: Me, too.
I really love the guy.
>> RODGER: I like him.
I like him. He's a good kid.
>> DEBB: But he's sick.
He's sick.
>> JEFF V.: Debb. She wants to
go, too, by the way.
>> ALICIA: Really?
>> JEFF V.: Yeah.
>> ALICIA: She told me that you
wanted to go.
She sure did.
>> JEFF V.: What?
>> ALICIA: She told me that you
wanted to go.
>> JEFF V.: That is a bald-faced
lie.
>> ALICIA: Okay, scandalous.
She told me you wanted to go.
>> DEBB: I-I'm going to probably
vote for Jeff.
And I was talking with him
today, you know, and he doesn't
even seem that upset at the
thought of it.
>> RODGER: Yeah.
>> DEBB: He's like... he wants a
pizza and a coke.
>> RODGER: He-he might've...
>> ALICIA: She said, "He's
falling apart, doesn't feel
good."
I was like, "Yeah, okay."
>> JEFF V.: Are you kidding me?
>> ALICIA: No, I'm not kidding
you.
I wouldn't tell you that if she
didn't say it.
>> JEFF V.: It's like there's a
part of me that's a little
paranoid about who's talking to
who.
I see these two standing over
across, um... Mike and Rodger
standing across the river
talking.
They're not fishing.
They're not doing anything.
They're just talking, and uh,
the wheels start turning, and
just... my eyes are going
around.
>> MICHAEL: I mean, it's two
different games, you know?
>> JEFF V.: Just because we've
said what we're doing doesn't
necessarily mean it's going to
happen, and I haven't been with
these people long enough to know
for sure how well...
I mean, I'm not going to trust
anybody, but there's a
certain... to a certain point,
you have to.
>> JEFF V.: I puked on camera.
How embarrassing.
>> MICHAEL: You puked?
>> DEBB: Couple times already.
>> MICHAEL: Did you save it?
>> DEBB: Would you stop?
( laughing )
>> KIMMI: It's like going to
court.
Tribal Council is going to
Nobody likes to go to court,
you know, but if you broke the
law, you got to go, and we broke
the law by not winning.
So we, you know, we got to go
face our punishment.
Our punishment... is to get rid
of one of our own.
>> MICHAEL: The people that I
think that are in jeopardy
tonight are potentially Jeff,
because of the health issues,
and Rodger might not be safe.
He could be a liability in the
challenges, and especially
swimming challenges and climbing
challenges.
And it's not just Rodger.
It would be anybody over 50
years old.
>> JEFF V.: I mean, I-I'm
looking forward to voting
somebody out, 'cause it's the
game, and I'm here to play the
game.
I'm not here to make friends.
I'm not here for that.
People have got to go, and I
look forward to walking up,
writing somebody's name on a
card and talking about 'em.
( laughs )
Um... I'm getting ready to do
it.
>> JEFF: Guys, come on in.
We begin your first Tribal
Council with a ritual.
Behind each of you is a torch.
Grab a torch and approach a
flame.
Dip your torches in and... get
some fire, put 'em back in their
slots.
We do this because fire does
represent life here.
These torches will now represent
your life, your identity at
Tribal Council.
You'll bring these torches with
you to each Tribal Council, and
the good news is when you return
home tonight, you will have
fire.
Before we get into this, I just
want you guys to take a second
and look around at where we're
at.
We're on top of a granite
waterfall.
Can't think of a more
spectacular place for the drama
that's going to go down here
every three days.
This is where you account for
your actions.
Some of those actions tonight
are going to help you.
Going to stay here a few more
days.
Some of those actions may come
back to haunt you.
One thing's for certain.
One of you guys will be the
first person voted out of a
tribe.
So before we get to that, let's
do a little gauge in how the
first few days were.
Debb, what about finding the
camp?
Was it a celebration or was it
fall down, "I'm exhausted"?
>> DEBB: Celebration.
Celebration.
It was celebration all the way
in.
Hop in the water and then regret
it afterwards when we were
freezing and had no fire.
>> JEFF: Yeah, let's talk a
little about that. Fire.
You've-you've been one really
trying to get this fire going.
Yeah, I been the one trying and
getting no fire.
I mean, I've tried everything
those damn books said to do.
The bow, the-the... this thing.
That's crazy.
>> JEFF: Well, you'll have fire
tonight when you go home.
>> DEBB: Yeah, yeah.
That's good to know.
It's been a little cold a couple
nights here.
>> JEFF: Have you guys formed
any impressions about the other
tribe in the limited time you've
seen them?
>> MICHAEL: We haven't really
had a lot of contact with them,
but, uh, right now, we totally
see them as the enemy.
We haven't had a chance to bond
with them.
We haven't had a chance to talk
with them at all.
I didn't even look at 'em when
we lost.
>> NICK: Yesterday's event was
just a physical challenge, and I
would've put money on us any day
to win that challenge, but they
went through, and then we had
problems.
>> JEFF: Rodger, leadership come
up?
Did anybody emerge as a leader?
>> RODGER: Uh, yes.
I would say probably, uh, Mike
has.
Uh, uh, as far as building the
hut, I think we both probably
shared in on that, 'cause my
knowledge on that is pretty
extensive in-in that I teach a
carpentry class, and, uh...
But overall, I'd say he's
probably taken the lead, and-and
that's fine, 'cause he's a very
knowledgeable person.
We all... we all get along
great.
Tonight is, uh, really a hard
deal for us.
Uh, personally, I-I thought that
the first vote off would be
easy, because you would probably
have somebody that would be
slacking, but we just haven't
had that.
I mean, every one of these
people have worked and worked
hard, and that's-that's what
makes tonight's vote so hard.
>> JEFF: All right, it's time to
vote.
Here's how it's going to work.
One by one, you guys will go
across the bridge to the voting
confessional.
You'll write down in big clear
letters the name of the person
you're voting for, hold it up,
speak your peace-- why you're
voting the way you're voting--
then fold it up, put it in the
voting container, come back and
have a seat.
Make sense?
We'll start here with you, Debb.
You're up.
>> DEBB: I love this guy dearly,
but I came here deciding that I
was going to vote on the
strongest surviving.
Jeff's been the sickest of all
of us, and he's still not over
it, so I'm going to vote for
Jeff, and I hate to do it.
I love him.
>> RODGER: No real reason,
actually.
She's as hard a worker as
anybody out there, and, uh...
somebody had to go.
>> KIMMI: I'm voting for Debb
because... she's a great worker
and everything, but she does
feel isolated.
You know, when we're together
all in the tent at night, she
just chooses... to be
independent, and... she's just a
strong-willed person.
It's not a bad thing.
It's just not what I need.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
I need to remind you that once
the votes are tallied, the
decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
You'll do so across this bridge
here.
Take the bridge up, over the
rocks, down to a confessional
where you can speak as long as
you want about your time here in
the Outback.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Debb.
Jeff.
Four votes for Debb, one vote
for Jeff.
First person voted out of the
tribe... is Debb.
No point in revealing the other
two votes.
You need to bring your torch.
>> DEBB: Do good. Kick ...
>> JEFF: Over here, Debb.
The tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> KIMMI: Good-bye, Debb.
>> JEFF: You survived your first
Tribal Council.
Grab your torches.
You'll have fire.
Head back to camp,
I'll see you tomorrow.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
Next time on Survivor, Kel is
accused of smuggling food.
>> MITCHELL: Jerri blatantly
said that she saw something that
looked just like beef jerky.
>> KEL: It was a blade of grass,
and I was chewing on that.
>> JERRI: It was nowhere near
any grass.
>> JEFF: Kimmi struggles with
the immunity challenge.
( screams )
You got cow brain there.
>> KIMMI: I can't eat a brain.
>> You're good.
>> DEBB: I wouldn't have minded
getting voted off if I had
fell... fallen during a
competition, if I was lazy, if I
wasn't a team player, but when I
come here, and I give all of
that, and I still get voted off,
I bet you if Jeff had read every
one of those votes, it would
have been seven to one, and
that's-that's a shame.
I still thought a lot of it
boiled down to mental toughness
and physical ability, and none
of that even mattered.