>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
The Barramundi camp was washed
away by a flash flood.
>> RODGER: Oh, God.
>> ELISABETH: Wow.
>> TINA: I saw the devastation,
and my first thought was, you
know, that's our home.
>> COLBY: It wiped everything
out, you know, including a good
portion of everybody's emotional
steam.
>> ELISABETH: Because this group
has really endured a lot, it's
tough to have to go and cast a
vote.
>> JEFF: At tribal council, the
Ogakor alliance turned on one of
their own, making Amber the 11th
person voted out.
Five remain.
Who will be the next to go?
>> RODGER: Going to try to get
everything cleaned off this
beach.
We never know when we're going
to have another torrential rain
like we had a couple of days
ago.
It took out everything.
>> ELISABETH: I woke up this
morning, and I was so wet on one
side.
I'm like, "Did I go to the
bathroom in my sleep," like, I
couldn't... I don't think I've
ever had that feeling because my
left side was just soaked from
the ground.
>> KEITH: It rained a lot last
night and our new shelter
leaked.
I didn't sleep all night.
Everyone was a little drained
this morning.
>> COLBY: The closer you get to
the end, the more you think
about what's waiting for you
when you leave, be it food, be
it your family, your bed, your
pillow.
>> TINA: I miss my husband and
my children more than anything.
I'm still kind of a newlywed.
I've only been married just a
year and a half, and my husband
is my very best friend.
And I miss picking my kids up
from school and having my son
happy to see me.
And I just miss everything about
them.
>> COLBY: With the storm that
came through and the shelter,
that's the worst I've seen Tina.
She was at a rock bottom.
But Elisabeth's been that way
for awhile.
Physically, Elisabeth's run
down, and emotionally, and she's
the one we've all tried to
nurture a little bit.
>> RODGER: I wish we had a
couple days without any rain,
that's what I wish.
It'd be nice.
>> ELISABETH: I woke up this
morning wet and still trying to
recover from being really
hungry.
The past four days really
wrecked me.
>> COLBY: See what our tree mail
says today.
>> KEITH: Oh, my gosh.
>> RODGER: Let's hold the end of
it.
>> COLBY: "For 34 days on
yourself you've relied.
It's your strength and your wits
that the challenge has tried.
Now you will trust in your loved
one or mom if you hope to win at
Survivor.com.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
E-mail?
>> COLBY: Oh, my gosh, we get to
compete against each other with
our loved ones online.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God!
You guys, this is awesome!
>> KEITH: Yeah!
>> COLBY: I've got chills right
now.
>> ELISABETH: I can't even
contain myself!
I can't even contain myself!
>> KEITH: Relax.
>> ELISABETH: I can't.
I can't.
The e-mail said that we will
rely on our loved one or my mom.
My mom is the... she's my hero,
like, she is just the most
amazing, strong woman.
She got through breast cancer
and chemo like a trouper, and
any time I think that things get
tough out here, I know what
she's been through.
She's my hero.
And with her, I can do anything.
Let's go get ready.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
Welcome to the Outback Internet
Cafe-- Survivor style.
>> COLBY: Whoo!
>> JEFF: Thanks to technology,
you're about to chat online with
your loved ones.
>> KEITH: Oh, isn't that
amazing.
>> JEFF: In fact, how well you
do in this challenge will really
be all up to your loved ones,
because they're going to be
playing this game right along
with you.
One at a time, you're going to
ask them a series of survival
trivia questions.
The loved one who answers the
most questions correctly will
determine which of you will win.
For the winner, a private 30-
minute chat with your loved ones
online.
When the winner's done chatting,
I'm going to give you this Visa
card.
$500 spending limit, where you
can buy whatever you want for
your loved ones.
Point, click, shop, 24 hours
later, they'll have a package
delivered.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: It wouldn't really be a
true Internet cafe if we didn't
have coffee and a Danish.
So as each of you come up here
to say your initial hellos, I'll
pour you a cup of coffee, pick
your favorite Danish.
All right, Tina, let's start
with you.
You look eager to say hi.
Have a seat.
Want a nice coffee?
>> TINA: Sure.
>> JEFF: And help yourself to a
Danish.
You have your husband Dale and
your son Taylor and your
daughter Katie.
>> TINA: Hello, family.
I sure miss you.
>> There she is.
That's your mom right there.
"Hello, family."
Hey, babe.
We love you and we...
>> TINA: Dale must be typing.
"Hel... lo."
>> T and K.
Cool.
>> TINA: "Hey, babe.
We love and miss you.
You go, girl.
Taylor, Dale and Katie."
>> JEFF: All right, Elisabeth,
come on up.
Okay, here's who's at home
waiting for you: your mom
Elisabeth, your dad Kenneth and
your brother Ken.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: I'm sensing a pattern
there.
>> ELISABETH: I love you
bunches.
Miss you more.
Safe and sound.
Love, Bessy.
Okay.
Send, okay.
>> It's Elisabeth.
"Love you bunches, miss you
more, safe and sound.
Love, Bessy."
>> ELISABETH: "Elisabeth, I
can't believe it's you.
Dad's here, Kenny is here.
What's happening there?"
I can't tell you.
Love you.
>> JEFF: Rodger, come on up.
Welcome.
>> RODGER: Thank you, buddy.
>> JEFF: Let me tell you who
you're talking to.
Your wife Pat, your daughter
Angela...
>> RODGER: Good.
>> JEFF: ...and your son-in-law
Kevin.
>> RODGER: Good.
Okay.
>> There it is.
>> "Hello, family.
Doing good.
I love you guys."
>> JEFF: Is that a little tear
in your eye?
>> RODGER: Yes, sir, it is.
Yep.
Here we go.
>> COLBY: What are they saying,
Rodge?
>> RODGER: How about you read
that?
>> JEFF: I'll read it for you.
"We are doing good.
We miss you and are very proud
of you."
>> RODGER: Whoo.
>> ELISABETH: Worth the wait,
Rodger.
>> RODGER: I knew I should have
brought my sunglasses.
>> JEFF: Come on up, Keith.
All right, Keith, Katrin ring a
bell?
Your sweetie?
She's there, waiting to hear
from you.
>> KEITH: We call each other
Peas and Carrots.
Hello, Peas, miss you so much.
I'll never be gone this long
from you again.
I love you.
>> Hello, Carrots.
You can call me Sweet Pea.
>> JEFF: Right on cue, huh?
>> "Hello, Carrots, you can call
me Sweet Pea.
I love you, too."
>> JEFF: Have a seat, Colby.
Help yourself to a Danish.
You've got Gaye, your mom.
>> COLBY: No way.
>> RODGER: Oh, wow.
>> COLBY: Sweet.
Hey, gang.
The Colbster is still alive.
I love you.
The best thing about this is
just being able to let her know
I'm still okay.
We're best friends, and it's so
much more than just a mother-son
relationship.
She's everything.
My mom just said, "Hi, baby."
She always calls me her baby boy
because my brother's older than
I am.
( sighs )
That's what I needed, right
there.
>> RODGER: I guess you guys
realize that us three men fell
apart worse than any of the
women did.
Very big strong men.
>> COLBY: I was pretty composed
until she responded.
>> RODGER: That was the way with
me.
>> COLBY: I thought I was doing
good until those words came
across the screen.
>> RODGER: Once the words came
up, that was it for me.
>> JEFF: Okay, let's start the
challenge.
Here's the deal: you're going to
each ask the same set of five
questions to your family.
The winner will be the person
whose family answers the most
questions correctly.
Tina, you're up.
Read off the questions and hit
"send."
>> TINA: Oh, my gosh, this is a
good question for all of us.
"In the Southern Hemisphere...
>> The sun rises in which
direction?"
It always rises in the east.
East is "C."
Question number two...
>> ELISABETH: "True or false,
the emu is the largest bird in
the world."
>> "The emu is the largest bird
in the world."
Okay, true.
Number three.
I have to get back to the
question.
>> RODGER: Question three: "Heat
cramps are caused by a loss of:
A: water; B: sugar..."
>> "Number C, salt,
number D, protein."
The answer is C.
Question number four:
>> KEITH: "Australia's famous
for its scary snakes.
Of the ten most venomous snakes
in the outback...
>> How many live in Australia?"
Oh, my God.
A: three, B: six, C: nine,
D: ten."
I have no idea.
A?
Number five: "If you are one
mile from a lightning strike...
>> COLBY: "Approximately how
long would it take to you hear
the thunder?
A: one second, B: three
seconds, C: five seconds,
D: seven seconds."
>> This sounds like it's
backward to me.
I'm going to say D: seven
seconds.
>> JEFF: Okay, ready for
the results?
First question: "In the southern
hemisphere, the sun rises in
which direction?"
Correct answer was C: East.
Second question: "The emu is
the largest bird on the world."
False.
Ostrich.
Third question: "Heat cramps are
caused by a loss of...
C: Salt."
>> TINA: Oh, gosh.
>> JEFF: Fourth question:
"Australia is famous for its
scary snakes.
Of the ten most venomous snakes
in the outback--" key word--
"...how many live in Australia?"
Obviously, all ten.
Last question:
>> ELISABEITH: Oh, my gosh.
>> TINA: Gosh.
>> JEFF: "If you are one mile
from a lightning strike,
approximately how long would it
take you to hear the thunder?"
It's a myth that it's one
second.
It is five seconds.
All right, before I announce the
winner, let's recap what you're
going to win.
30 minutes online with your
family, $500 shopping spree,
courtesy of Visa, and for the
rest of you, one final moment to
say good-bye.
Winning the reward with four
correct answers-- Tina.
>> RODGER: Okay!
Go for it!
>> JEFF: Congratulations, Tina.
>> TINA: It feels good to win
something, for heaven sakes!
>> JEFF: All right, Rodger, you
get one last good-bye.
>> RODGER: You will not believe
the things I have saw and done.
I love you guys.
I told you I was going to...
need those.
>> COLBY: She said, "I will
fatten you up when you get home.
We all love you and miss you,
and can hardly wait for you to
be home.
Keep smiling and continue the
adventure.
Love, your mom."
>> ELISABETH: "Elisabeth, sorry
we didn't come through..."
Don't be sorry.
"We love you and we're so proud
of you.
We pray for you every day.
Kisses and hugs."
>> KEITH: I can only think of
one important question that came
to me one night as a shooting
star shot across the sky at some
wee hours of the morning: will
you marry me, Peas?
>> COLBY: Oh, my gosh.
Hope you were expecting
something like this.
>> RODGER: You did it.
You did it.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my gosh!
>> Oh, my God.
"Will you marry me, Peas?"
Oh, my God.
Are you serious?
>> ELISABETH: Can you imagine
being on the other end of this,
though.
>> TINA: Would you type that
response again?
I'm not sure I read that right.
>> KEITH: "Yes!"
Yes!
Yes.
"You caught me off guard.
I've missed you more than words
can say.
I'm sorry I missed the cues.
It has been a long week.
I love you and hope to see you
soon.
Yes!"
>> TINA: Congratulations, Keith.
>> ELISABETH: Whoo, whoo!
Wow!
>> JEFF: All right, Tina.
The throne is yours.
>> TINA: Whenever I got on the
computer, I could not type fast
enough.
I said, "We won.
Of all the things that I wanted
to win, this was it.
I wanted to talk to you all so
much."
I got a major rush from getting
to go talk to my family.
And I thought that's enough to
carry me through another eight
days, easy.
I love and miss you all more
than you will ever know, and I
will never ever go away again
for this long.
I thought, "Eight more days?
Got it beat, girl."
>> RODGER: Best day out here.
Rewards challenge, and we all
won, every one of us.
>> KEITH: Everybody won today.
>> RODGER: We all got to talk to
our families back home.
>> COLBY: I mean, even in the
rain... it's finally soaked
through my shorts and my boots.
My feet are soaking wet, and I'm
still... I have a grin on
my face.
>> TINA: After I won my reward,
the main emotion was sheer joy.
>> ELISABETH: Look at this, a
little recreation going on.
>> COLBY: Nice!
>> TINA: I mean my mouth hurt
from just smiling the whole time
I was typing.
Just the few words that we got
to exchange between one another,
it was just sheer joy.
>> COLBY: Hey, Tina, Keith's
going to say grace.
>> KEITH: Dear God, thank you
for today.
It was an incredible day.
On a personal note, thank you
for the "yes" from my
sweetheart, Katrin.
And keep sending those prayers
back home for loved ones to
know that we miss them.
Keep them safe and continue to
keep us safe in our last few
days.
And we really thank you for this
opportunity and the experience
we've had in the outback.
Amen.
>> ALL: Amen.
>> COLBY: I think it was
apparent to everyone here that
today, at least for a day,
strategy did not enter in our
heads.
And that probably won't be the
case tomorrow.
But today, we didn't care about
winning a million bucks.
>> RODGER: It's going to be a
cold, cold night tonight.
>> TINA: Colby, you're the
candle blower outer.
Good night, everybody.
>> KEITH: Good night.
See you in the morning.
>> COLBY: Lights are out.
Keith, are you ready?
>> KEITH: Yes, sir.
( thunder crashing )
>> KEITH: Rodger and I are
usually up the first time, you
know, before anybody.
We had a bad night of rain, so
anytime we have rain, we more
than likely lose our fire.
Starting a fire in the morning
is really very, very difficult.
We were out just doing our
morning bathroom break, and I
looked off to the horizon.
I said, "What is that smoke over
there?"
We found an actual piece of tree
that was smoldering from a
forest fire that was probably
two weeks old.
God's giving us a present this
morning on this cold, wet
morning.
That was a huge find for us.
It was the basis behind a great
fire.
>> RODGER: Do you believe that?
I literally cannot believe that.
>> KEITH: You can see how a
caveman learned about fire and
captured it, picked it up,
brought it back to where he was
at.
>> RODGER: And that's how they
started having weenie roasts.
>> KEITH: That was it.
>> TINA: Looking at the river,
it's running through our old
camp.
That is truly amazing.
>> COLBY: Wow.
From a material standpoint,
we've lost a lot.
I mean, we have our rice, and
now that we know we have food,
we rationed the rice for the
amount of days that we have
left.
>> ELISABETH: How much do we
have left?
>> RODGER: Two bags of brown
rice and a bag of white rice.
>> COLBY: Keith is cooking way
too much rice at every meal.
All you've got to do is just
make smaller servings and he
just... he can't get it through
his head.
>> KEITH: This is where the game
is really on right now.
My intention is that I'll be
here with Colby and Tina in the
last three.
At this stage of the game, it's
natural that political
campaigning is going on,
especially with these last few
individuals, because they're
your jury.
I'm doing a lot more of the
cooking now, now it's more one-
on-one dynamic, it's important
to be able to do things that the
other members of the group see
as a value.
Let me try something on this--
a little experiment here.
>> ELISABETH: Keith just said,
"I'm going to do a little
experiment with the brown rice
and white rice."
I mean, our portions were huge.
And he said, "You know, I'm used
to doing this sort of thing.
I can I assess how much we
have."
I think he just feels awfully
comfortable with the fact that
he's going to be one of the
final three or two, and he knows
the portion sizes will be bigger
then.
>> COLBY: Isn't that rice
cooked?
>> KEITH: Just cooked a little
bit of it.
It's okay, I blended it in with
the white.
The brown rice cooks up and
expands so much more; gives you
more volume.
>> COLBY: Keith, you said the
exact opposite five days ago.
You said the brown rice yields
less.
>> KEITH: No, I said you have to
use more water.
>> COLBY: No, you said it yields
less.
You said it three times in a
row.
>> KEITH: I said, if you don't
use more water.
>> COLBY: Put half a cup ration.
We decided on that and we have
not stuck to it in the last
four meals.
>> KEITH: Colby...
>> COLBY: I'm not going to do
this ration thing again, where
we run out of rice, Keith.
>> KEITH: We're fine.
>> COLBY: We were... we're
eating fine.
>> KEITH: Okay, we will be
fine.
I'll check it again, but I'm
sure we're more than fine.
>> ELISABETH: Check it right
after we eat.
>> KEITH: Yeah, I actually
checked it before we ate,
actually.
The rice issue today was the
first time I've seen Colby blow
up-- and it got me legitimately
concerned, especially when
Elisabeth was right there,
chiming in.
I thought there's something
going on here and I'm really in
a very vulnerable situation.
>> COLBY: We had 14 days worth
of rice with 12 days left, and
we're now breaking even.
>> ELISABETH: ...with the brown
rice, which doesn't even equal
the white.
>> KEITH: No, it does equal.
>> COLBY: No, it doesn't, Keith.
You're arguing yourself is what
you're doing because you said
two times in a span of five
minutes that brown rice does not
yield the same amount as white
rice.
>> KEITH: I said you have to use
more water to cook with.
>> COLBY: No, you didn't.
He's a fool.
The guy's a bozo, and I'm just
tired of it.
I'm tired of dealing with him.
I don't take anything that Keith
does for face value.
I think there's an ulterior
motive to everything he says and
everything he does, whether it's
cooking rice or proposing to his
girlfriend on-line.
I don't like the way he's
playing the game.
I think he's trying way too
hard because he can't make it on
just being who he is.
My game with Keith is done.
It's over.
>> KEITH: The rice cakes worked
beautifully.
>> COLBY: As far as what's
wearing on me the most: time.
The long days.
That's the only thing getting to
me, nothing else.
And if it weren't for the long
days, Keith wouldn't even get to
me.
I mean, I wouldn't be as
volatile as I am if it wasn't
for the boredom.
>> KEITH: Not unusual to sit and
look at the fire for an hour and
just stare at the fire and the
flames.
>> COLBY: Your fire becomes
what's been referred to as the
"outback television."
I mean, and that's what it is.
That's your entertainment.
You look and see how long an
ember can burn or how long it
takes a log to burn in half to
where it collapses.
It's just one of those things.
You color in a coloring book or
you play a few games of
backgammon.
Or you get into a conversation
with someone that you forgot you
had three days ago.
>> TINA: Make, like, red
cardboard paper and then I put
the white doilies in the center.
In my kitchen, in my dining
room, we have hearts.
You just have to walk through
them all throughout the house.
>> COLBY: Cold, hunger, wet--
none of that can compare to the
boredom.
It doesn't even fit in the same
category, as far as I'm
concerned.
>> RODGER: I literally cannot
stand, like, to go up there and
just lay around in that hut for
three or four hours, just drives
me crazy.
I said I got to get up and get
out of here.
I said I can't stay in this hut
laying around.
( groans )
>> COLBY: Rodger's always
chipped in more than he's had to
with the tribe, whether it be
fishing or boiling water.
He's always up to do stuff.
Being the oldest guy still here,
he's got more energy than any of
us do, you know, and I think it
comes from his heart.
>> RODGER: Out by the bathroom,
I found some more bark.
>> COLBY: Because we're not
playing for ourselves now,
we're playing for those who are
deserving to be here.
Rodger and Elisabeth and Tina
are all three deserving to be in
the final three.
As far as Keith goes, there's
not anything outstanding or
phenomenal that he's done that
has kept him in the game.
>> KEITH: Immunity plays a huge
part in this because immunity
could mean anyone can be along
farther in the game.
And at this point, anybody could
win.
>> RODGER: Up through here
somewhere, the nearest path.
Look at that.
Five lanterns.
And a log.
Want to take it back up there
before we open it?
>> COLBY: Yeah, let's do that.
There's an old lock and the
message reads like this: "Many
of the first settlers came as
prisoners here.
They'd escape into the outback,
no water, no food, no beer.
Your next challenge is a jail
break.
These lamps will light your way.
And if you listen carefully, in
the final four you'll stay."
I think it'll be fun.
It'll be interesting.
>> KEITH: This will be a blast.
>> COLBY: Yeah.
>> JEFF: Hey, guys.
>> ELISABETH: Hi, Jeff.
>> JEFF: I'll start by taking
the immunity necklace, since
you're shackled.
Immunity back up for grabs
tonight.
Now, the reason you're shackled:
the reason is because the first
settlers here in the outback
were themselves prisoners.
In a minute, I'm going to tell
you a story about these
prisoners, and when I'm
finished, you're going to use
the information in that story to
free yourself.
You're going to make your way
through this abandoned cattle
station where there are eight
different questions based on the
story.
Each correct answer to a
question gives you a key, and
that key will open up any one of
your five locks.
However, if you answer the
question wrong, you won't be
able to open the lock, and you
must move on to another one of
the eight stations.
You continue making your way
through the stations till you've
unlocked all five shackles.
The first person back here
completely freed carrying their
open shackles and their locks
wins immunity.
Okay, here's the story: the
first settlers were prisoners
brought over here from Great
Britain.
Now, occasionally, a prisoner
tried to escape, but the only
place they had to go was into an
early grave because these
escapees, known as bolters,
lacked one basic thing-- they
lacked basic survival skills.
Sun was their number one enemy.
Temperatures can reach upwards
of 110 degrees.
You can live for 30 days without
food.
Dehydration will kill you in
three days.
Prisoners tried to fight this by
taking off their clothes, which
exacerbated the dehydration
process.
And, in spite of how arid it is
out here, a lot of sources of
water, if you know where to
look.
Same with food.
You've tasted some of the food
from the outback.
Mangrove worms, even spiny leaf
insects, which are a better
source of protein than the
bigger lizards.
You get tired of bugs and
reptiles, bats will lead you to
large fruit that is colorless
but edible.
Birds will lead you to fruit
that is pretty but inedible.
Their sense of geography was so
skewed that they thought China
and India were just around the
corner, thinking China was only
150 miles from Australia.
Had they known some basic
skills, they could have found
their way.
For example, when visible during
the summer months, the Seven
Sisters constellation shows you
which way is south.
So the conditions out here were
very tough, but they weren't
insurmountable.
Aboriginals have lived out here
since 38,000 BC, which proves
that people can and do learn to
survive.
Now we're going to see what you
guys have learned.
Let's play.
Survivors, ready?
For immunity, go!
>> TINA: The lock is killing my
shin.
>> COLBY: "According to
prisoner's flawed geography,
what country was just 150 miles
from Australia?"
>> KEITH: "How long have
Aboriginal people been living in
Australia?"
40,000 years.
>> RODGER: "In which season is
the Seven Sisters constellation
not visible?"
Summer.
Dad gummit.
>> TINA: Okay.
"To avoid dehydration from
the blazing sun, it's better
to...?"
"Remove clothing, wear
clothing."
Okay...
Okay.
Come on.
Get out.
>> ELISABETH: "What was the
slang for an escaped prisoner?"
Stepper.
Oh, no, that's wrong.
>> COLBY: "When searching for
fruit, it's best to follow
the..."
>> RODGER: "Pound for pound,
which is a better source of
protein?
Insect or lizard?"
Insect or lizard?
I'm going to go with lizard.
( sighs )
>> TINA: "Death by dehydration
occurs how many times faster
than death by starvation?"
Ooh...
>> ELISABETH: Come on.
I guess not.
>> KEITH: Come on, come on, come
on, come on.
>> RODGER: "Death by dehydration
occurs how many times faster
than death by starvation?"
Five times.
I thought that was the wrong
answer.
>> ELISABETH: "What country was
just..."
>> COLBY: "To avoid dehydration
from the blazing sun..."
>> RODGER: 20,000 years.
>> ELISABETH: "To avoid
dehydration from the blazing
sun..."
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
>> KEITH: "How many times...?"
Ten times.
Come on.
"When searching for
fruit..."
Bats.
>> TINA: Is that not right?
Guess it's not right.
>> KEITH: Oh, yes, come on,
it should work.
I need this.
>> JEFF: Got them all?
>> KEITH: I don't know, I don't
know.
One, two, three.
>> JEFF: Keith, that's just
four.
Got to have all five to win,
bud.
>> KEITH: Shoot, where's my one
lock at?
>> JEFF: Got 'em?
Let me see them.
>> KEITH: Damn it.
>> COLBY: Hands and ankles.
That's it.
>> JEFF: Immunity.
>> COLBY: Sweet, baby!
>> JEFF: Got immunity: Colby.
>> KEITH: Damn!
You beat me!
>> COLBY: What'd you forget?
>> KEITH: My lock, I lost a lock
running with it.
Good job.
>> JEFF: Let me present this to
you again.
How many times in a row have you
had immunity?
>> COLBY: Three times.
>> JEFF: Three times, man.
You are tough.
>> COLBY: Thank you very much.
>> JEFF: You're safe tomorrow
night.
You four are vulnerable.
I know you're a tight group.
Part of the game.
Head back to camp.
I'll see you tomorrow night at
tribal council.
>> RODGER: I don't know what's
going to happen at tonight's
tribal council.
I got the impression that it
would probably be myself and
Elisabeth, not necessarily in
that order, would be the next
two to be voted off.
Well, Tina mentioned which one
I felt needed the money the
worst: myself or Elisabeth.
I said I think Elisabeth
probably does because of, uh,
Elisabeth's background and her
mother being sick and what have
you.
And I just decided that I would
take the out first for
Elisabeth.
I was the chief executive
officer in a bank for 12 years,
so, you know...
>> TINA: That makes me feel real
good to hear.
>> RODGER: Yeah.
So Elisabeth's a nice young
lady.
I think about as much of her as
I do a lot of members of my
family.
I really do.
>> TINA: I do, too.
>> RODGER: Yeah, an awful sweet
girl.
When somebody's got medical
bills-- here she comes.
I really wouldn't want Elisabeth
to know that I had done that.
But Elisabeth and myself have
become very close, and I've kind
of watched out for her.
And that's basically it, really.
Basically the reason.
I'll share my seat there with
you.
I'm just sitting there, we're
just sitting there yacking and
I'm so rude.
>> ELISABETH: You are, Rodger.
That's what I think of you,
rude.
>> KEITH: Rodger just wanted it
to be known that when it comes
to picking Elisabeth or himself
to go first, he wanted to go
first.
But you don't know what's really
going to happen.
I could be voted off tonight and
totally blindsided.
>> ELISABETH: Tribal council is
more up in the air than I would
have thought tonight.
Colby supposedly was voting for
Rodger, and I don't know if
Keith has driven him crazy
enough that he'll vote for
Keith.
>> TINA: Everybody have their
bag?
>> COLBY: The biggest struggle I
deal with in the final few
tribal councils is whether I
want to sit beside someone who
almost guarantees me the million
bucks or whether I want to sit
beside someone who, if I don't
win the million bucks, I'll
still feel good about that other
person winning.
I don't even have my answer to
that.
I did yesterday, but it changed
this morning and it'll change
again tonight.
>> JEFF: We'll bring in the jury
now.
I'll once again remind you not
to address the jury.
As we wind down to six days
left, certainly the information
they gather at tribal councils
becomes increasingly
significant.
Keith, how big of an impact does
daily life have at this point?
You wake up in the morning with
one idea of who you're going to
vote out tonight.
By the time you get here, it's
completely different.
Is that plausible, possible?
>> KEITH: You know, you play a
lot of mind games with yourself.
I mean, you are your own worst
player at this stage of the game
because you're constantly
second-guessing your thought
process and, you know, you're
confident here and then you're
not confident there, and...
This game, as I keep saying,
"expect the unexpected"
because... it's where it is
right now.
>> JEFF: Is there a sense of
paranoia that takes over?
You see two people huddled in
the corner, you think, "I know
they're talking about me,
they're going to vote me out
tonight."
Is that starting to happen?
>> TINA: Absolutely.
Whenever there's this few people
left, and you think, "This is
closer than I thought and I
could make it, you know?
I've only got six days left."
And then you see some people
whispering and you're like, "Oh,
my gosh, I could go tonight."
You do.
You start getting nervous and
paranoid and then your whole
day's blown, you know, because
you don't know what's going to
happen.
>> JEFF: 36 days you guys have
spent together.
Some relationships have formed,
even ones I can see from the
outside.
Elisabeth, tell me about the
relationship with Rodger,
because you guys seem to have
really connected.
>> ELISABETH: Rodger is... I
call him my "outback daddy."
He just really is.
And from the moment I saw him, I
knew that there was something
special.
We've become friends.
I feel safe with Rodger around,
and Rodger's my man.
I love him.
>> JEFF: Rodger, how's it feel
to have somebody say such kind
words about you?
>> RODGER: Well, I'm very, very
flattered.
But I could very easily turn the
tables back on Elisabeth.
She's a fine young lady.
Character-wise, morals-wise and
she's tops in my book.
>> JEFF: Keith, when you look at
Colby with that immunity
necklace, knowing if you hadn't
dropped one of your locks, you'd
be wearing it tonight, what goes
through your mind?
Do you care at all?
>> KEITH: You know, of course I
wish I had it around my neck,
but that's the way the cookie
crumbles.
That was the way the game was
played, and it was all fair, and
I dropped the lock, and it was
my faux pas, and that's just the
way it goes, part of the game.
What are you going to do?
Can't cry over spilled milk.
>> JEFF: All right, guys.
11 torches behind me, five left.
Another torch is going to join
that tonight.
Let's vote.
Elisabeth, you're up.
>> ELISABETH: This is a great
group, but, Keith, I think that
you've been a little
overconfident and cocky about
how you're going to be here till
the very end.
>> KEITH: Old buddy, I look
forward to that home-cooked meal
in Kentucky.
And if it's my time to go, I
can't wait to see you on the
outside.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are tallied, the
decision is final.
The person voted out of the
tribe will be asked to leave the
tribal council area immediately.
First vote...
Keith.
Rodger.
Two votes Rodger, two votes
Keith.
One vote left.
Rodger.
Need to bring me your torch,
>> RODGER: See you guys.
See you, kiddo.
>> JEFF: Rodger, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode and hear
what Rodger has to say.
Next time on Survivor...
Only four remain of Barramundi,
and the outback has taken its
toll on all of them.
>> ELISABETH: My hair is falling
out.
My hair is falling out.
>> JEFF: And a surprise guest
visits the remaining survivors.
>> ELISABETH: Whoo-hoo!
>> TINA: Welcome to Barramundi!
>> RODGER: I was the oldest
person getting off the plane, 53
years old.
I've been out here 36 days and
just had six more to go.
I could've done without food
for those next six days, if I'd
had to, to stayed out here.
I wish them all the luck and I
especially wish the best of luck
to Elisabeth.
I hope she goes all the way.
Thank you.