>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Michael was determined to make a
kill.
>> MICHAEL: This is the pig-
killer.
>> JEFF V.: His stupid spear.
"I'm going to go catch pigs.
Go get me a pig."
>> JEFF: At Ogakor, Jerri and
Colby whispered sweet nothings
to each other
>> COLBY: Black coffee, or cream
and sugar?
>> JERRI: Cream and sugar.
I'm such a sucker for cowboys.
>> JEFF: In the toughest
challenge yet, Kucha won
immunity...
( cheering )
...sending Ogakor to Tribal
Council, where lines were drawn
when Jerri made it clear who her
friends were.
>> JERRI: I've been very
fortunate in my ability to bond
with Amber, Mitchell and Colby.
>> JEFF: But there was no bond
with Maralyn, who was voted out
of the tribe.
It's time for you to go.
13 remain.
Tonight, one more will go.
>> TINA: I had slept outside
last night, as did Keith.
We were the first ones up, so we
thought the first ones up, let's
just get up and go fishing this
morning.
So we cleared everything off the
boat, got the fishing rods
together.
Jerri popped up out of the tent,
ran, turned over the canoe...
and acted like she was going to
get ready to go fishing.
>> MITCHELL: You guys wanna go?
( canister rattling )
You're going to take this?
>> KEITH: Yeah.
Jerri and the others, they
wanted to take the canoe out.
You know, we said, "Well, we're
just getting ourselves ready,
we've got all our gear, we're
getting ready to go."
"Oh, we were going to do that."
Well, isn't that ironic, you
know, just 'cause we were going
to go?
>> TINA: Well, that's why we
were going to go, because you
guys were sleeping, so...
( Jerri groans )
I just said "Look, you know, we
were gonna go fishing.
You all were asleep.
We're going to go fishing."
And apparently, Keith wanted to
have a talk with me, so he said,
"Well, Tina, let's just go walk
along the bank and fish that
way."
>> KEITH: At Tribal Council last
night, Tina and I had an
opportunity to get a little bit
better understanding of where we
sit within our own tribe.
When Jerri was asked the
question who her friends are,
she made a point of mentioning
Amber, Colby, Mitchell and
herself, that they all get along
best.
And then, of course, she wanted
to make sure that everybody was
clear that she was here to win
the money.
And she's going to do whatever
she has to to win the money.
So, Tina and I were a little
miffed by that.
>> TINA: You have four or five
young people playing.
You know, they've got so much
chemistry that it is almost
second nature just to-- whoo--
just immediately gravitate
towards one another.
And it makes me feel kind of
like an outsider, which I am an
outsider at this point.
>> JERRI: It's all I can do to
keep from just laughing out
loud.
At Tribal Council, Jeff asked me
who I felt I had built
friendships with.
And immediately after I said it,
I kind of sucked it back up,
because I realized I was
basically challenging people to
vote for me.
Which doesn't put me in a very
good position.
>> KEITH: Jerri is perfect for
this game.
She will ride the team until
it's time to take the knife out
and cut someone's throat.
>> JERRI: That was good stuff.
>> KEITH: I didn't come out here
to be pushed around by a
bartender-wannabe-actress.
Maybe it's time just to shake
her world up a little bit.
I can tell you one thing: Tina
and I are not going to go down
without a fight.
I came here to win the money,
but now my motive isn't to win
the money, but to do everything
I can to make sure she does not
win the money.
>> ALICIA: Wow, what is it?
>> RODGER: I have no idea.
>> ALICIA: You guys are not
going to believe this one.
>> KIMMI: What?
>> RODGER: We got a chicken egg.
>> ALICIA: We have a real egg.
>> RODGER: "For a change of the
menu, you must work with great
haste.
Build a pen on your beach, and
slide the pieces in place."
This morning, we received tree
mail.
And I went out there to it, and
it was a bird's nest.
And it involves a challenge of
building a chicken coop.
>> ALICIA: Grab one end.
( indistinct voices )
>> KIMMI: Okay, all of these are
pretty much straight.
I definitely have to appear that
I'm into this challenge, because
my head was on the chopping
block-- I know, with a couple of
people-- because of, um... you
know, my almost not eating the
worm and the cow brain thing.
At least this chicken coop thing
is a little bit of a change of
pace.
I know it might seem ironic,
because I don't eat mammals.
You know, I haven't had poultry
in over ten years, and I haven't
had red meat in over 15 years,
but if it boosts up morale for
these guys, it's going to be
good.
>> NICK: Oh, yeah.
>> MICHAEL: See, what I can do
is I can pry this over with my
pry bar here...
>> JEFF V.: I want those
chickens so bad.
For one reason, so Mike will
quit fishing and walking around
here flexing his muscle.
I really want chicken.
And I'm not above snatching it
out of the other team's arms.
I want a chicken.
>> JEFF: Okay, today's challenge
is a reward challenge.
And the map to your reward is
scrambled in a puzzle.
The first tribe to completely
unscramble their puzzle gets
three egg-laying chickens and
one rooster.
Big reward, a lot of eggs.
Pick your spots, and we'll get
started.
Playing for three egg-laying
chickens and a rooster.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Back it up, back it up, back
it up.
>> MITCHELL: Go around, rotate,
rotate...
>> AMBER: Bring this one up and
we'll bring this one down, over
here.
>> COLBY: Right here.
>> KEITH: No... slide it over...
>> JERRI: That one, that one
down.
>> RODGER: You got it made.
>> KIMMI: Okay, well, we have
this whole side, so now we can
work this... we got to do this
piece...
>> NICK: Yeah, swing this one
like this.
Goes... no, leave that.
>> RODGER: Doesn't that blue
piece right there go with...?
>> NICK: It goes in the middle.
>> RODGER: It goes in the
middle, that's right.
>> KIMMI: Those two need to be
together.
That should be one, two, three.
>> COLBY: No, no, no, no.
( indistinct voices )
>> ALICIA: That one he's got his
hand on.
>> KIMMI: Okay, hold on, hang
on, hang on.
>> ALICIA: Get off of this
table.
>> MICHAEL: Get off, Kimmi.
>> KIMMI: Well, what...?
( indistinct voices )
>> JEFF V.: What goes with it?
>> ALICIA: This one goes with
it.
>> JEFF V.: There goes the top
corner.
>> KEITH: Wait a minute, look,
look, look, look, look.
This goes here, and we're done.
>> AMBER: I say... just start
doing stuff.
>> KIMMI: That piece goes right
here.
>> JEFF V.: You had it right.
>> KIMMI: No, that was right.
That one goes over...
>> JEFF V.: You had it right.
>> KIMMI: That-that goes down.
This goes over.
( indistinct voices )
( all cheering )
>> JEFF: Good job.
( indistinct voices )
>> JEFF: This is your map to
your reward.
Got to figure out where you're
at, where you need to go.
>> NICK: No, wait, think about
perspective.
This is our blue, and that's
their green.
>> ALICIA: Yeah, "X" marks the
spot.
>> ELISABETH: You guys, we're
going straight.
>> ALICIA: There they are.
( whooping )
Hello, my lovelies.
( clucking )
( Elisabeth squawks )
>> JEFF V.: We got chickens.
>> ALICIA: Henrietta, Polly,
Ruby and Rocky.
>> JEFF V.: Hey, Henrietta, hey,
Ruby.
>> ALICIA: We all have to decide
who's going to kill one.
>> ELISABETH: I can't believe
I'm holding a chicken.
>> RODGER: Just don't hesitate
about putting him in.
Get him down in there.
>> KIMMI: Don't break her wings,
though.
>> RODGER: Who's next?
>> ALICIA: You're gonna squeeze
four chickens in there?
>> KIMMI: It's wrong.
>> NICK: They're giving you eggs
and protein and vitamins and all
that good stuff, okay?
>> KIMMI: Can't they give us
some edamame, some tofu?
>> ELISABETH: It's a good thing,
you guys.
You guys, we just won a reward.
It's like, everyone just smile
for a second-- whoo, reward!
>> MICHAEL: I felt when we won
the chickens, "Oh, no, I'm
unnecessary for food now."
They could eat a chicken every
other day and be totally fine,
until the merger.
And I thought to myself,
"Consume those chickens as
quickly as possible so we're
back to being hungry again."
( clucking )
>> RODGER: Shh...
>> NICK: We woke up in the
morning, Rodger and I, relocated
the chicken coop, got them
comfortable.
And then all of a sudden I
see Mike preparing to kill the
rooster.
Everybody else is sleeping, and
I said, "Let's wake up, figure
out what our day schedule is a
little bit more before we kill
it because if we had killed that
rooster, a lot of people would
have been upset.
We have to make decisions as a
group for us to get along.
...we should decide as a group
when we're going to eat it.
>> RODGER: That's-that's what I
asked him...
>> MICHAEL: That's what I just
asked you.
>> NICK: We don't need one
today.
( rooster crowing )
>> ELISABETH: That one's going
first.
>> AMBER: There's a fire.
You can actually hear the trees
falling down and burning.
>> TINA: You can hear it.
I'll put on my tennis shoes.
It seems to be getting closer
and closer.
You can see ash blowing in the
wind.
We have no idea how close it is
to our camp, even though we know
that it has to cross the water
in order to get to us.
>> AMBER: It's a concern, um...
But you know, I think we'll be
safe, as long as we head for the
water and everybody does the
right thing.
>> TINA: And you don't realize
that you're nothing to Jerri?
She said, "I'm in it to win,"
and you know, she's going to do
whatever it takes to win.
>> MITCHELL: Yeah.
>> TINA: She sees that we've got
the fishing poles out, jumps
out, grabs the boat, turns it
over.
And it's like she has to have
her way.
>> COLBY: Yeah.
>> TINA: And I am so over it, I
just can't hardly stand it.
I mentioned my frustration with
Jerri because it's building.
I don't know if it's just me.
Do other people feel the same
way I feel?
>> COLBY: It's going to get a
lot worse before it gets better.
>> TINA: I'm sorry.
She's the most bossy,
domineering person I've ever
met.
>> COLBY: She's coming, by the
way.
>> MITCHELL: Mm-hmm.
( sighs )
>> TINA: It was a little bit of
it just wanting to see how
strong does Mitch and Colby
align with Jerri.
And my thought was, if I could
get Colby, that would be two of
us.
And then maybe Colby could talk
to Amber, and that would be the
only chance that I would have to
make it.
At this point, I don't have
anything to lose.
>> COLBY: I had to get out of
the tent.
There's a little estrogen
overload in the tent right now,
and I just couldn't deal with
that.
Tina was taking things way too
personally.
>> KEITH: What happened last
night at Tribal Council is what
really set Tina and I apart.
Jeff said, "Well, who are your
friends?" and Jerri named, you
know, four individuals.
>> COLBY: Right.
>> KEITH: And Tina and I are
sitting on the sideline.
So that was, you know...
Tina and I just figured, "Well,
it's just a matter of time now."
>> COLBY: The powers that be
have predetermined long ago the
pecking order here, and also the
elimination order.
And, uh, Keith is up.
Keith and I have spent a lot of
time together.
Part of my reason for doing it--
one, we get along.
Two, we need Keith right now, so
the last thing I'm going to do
is alienate him.
>> KEITH: I'm cohabiting with
people who... what do I do with
these people?
>> COLBY: Yep.
>> KEITH: Who knows, man?
You and Jerri could get married.
>> COLBY: I know that ain't
happening.
>> KEITH: Tell you straight on
right now, she ain't good enough
for you.
And you know, it's cool you guys
got your little thing going, but
I'm gonna tell you right now,
she ain't no way good enough for
you.
>> COLBY ( laughs ): That's
funny.
>> KEITH: I would beat you like
a dog if I found out you two
hooked up.
>> COLBY ( laughs ): Well,
thanks, bro.
>> KEITH: That girl would cut
your throat in a heartbeat.
>> COLBY: Yeah, you're right.
( Rocky crowing )
>> RODGER: Everybody's on the
same wavelength-- we want to
have chicken today.
>> MICHAEL: I got a confirmation
from Nick and Jeff, and
Elisabeth said yes.
And if us four are saying yes,
everybody says yes.
>> KIMMI: I say no. Okay.
( sputtering laughter )
I guess that doesn't work.
>> ALICIA: Nope. I say do it
whenever you want to do it.
Just let me know when.
>> KIMMI: Yeah, 'cause I want to
know...
>> RODGER: Well, we've got to
get the water going.
I would love to have fried
chicken tonight.
It would be the first meal where
we didn't have to pass a piece
of fish around six or seven
times and everybody take a bite
of it.
Everybody would have their own
piece of chicken.
>> MICHAEL: Oh, it's boiling.
>> RODGER: Boiling?
>> MICHAEL: Boiling.
Rodger...
Do we need anything besides
tools?
>> RODGER: Just a hatchet and
a block of wood.
>> KIMMI: Alicia, I'm leaving.
>> ALICIA: Bye, sweetie.
I know it's harder for her.
>> RODGER: Just gotta look at
it, it's no different than
eating them fish we've been
eating.
I'm gonna hold his wings.
Just-just make it a good... one
good, clean blow.
( gentle crunching )
>> ALICIA: Mm, mm, mm!
>> MICHAEL: Everybody was loving
the chickens.
This could be the end of the
game for me, because they no
longer need me for a food
source.
It ups the stakes definitely for
me to catch the food.
But to stay in the limelight is
going to be harder and harder
because you've got to keep one-
upping yourself.
I caught one fish, and then I
caught a bigger one, then I
caught three fish, then I caught
five fish.
What am I going to do now,
wrestle an alligator?
( laughs )
>> JEFF V.: I'll take a chicken
over fish any day.
>> NICK: Once you go dark meat,
you don't ever go back.
( laughing )
( bird cawing )
>> MITCHELL: I'm just weak.
I'm hungry, I'm tired,
physically, emotionally, I'm
gone.
I feel that I think the most
about strategies, 'cause first
of all, I don't have much else
to think about.
And second of all, I want to go
far with this.
After seeing Colby and Keith
talking over in the water for a
couple of hours, who knows what
he's trying to convince Colby,
but you know what?
Maybe he's just kind of taking
Keith for a ride.
Colby had been talking a lot to
Keith.
We know Keith is trying to rear
something up from behind to try
to take one of us out.
>> JERRI: The only way it would
work is if Keith convinced Tina
and Colby...
>> AMBER: And Colby.
>> JERRI: ...to vote against me.
>> AMBER: Right, then...
>> JERRI: And you and us three
voted against Keith.
It would be three and three.
>> AMBER: A tie.
>> JERRI: And then you and me
with the most votes, I'd be
gone.
>> AMBER: Yep.
>> JERRI: This is definitely the
first time I've felt a little
bit threatened.
And I guess I deserve it after
making that pompous remark at
Tribal Council.
>> AMBER: Colby could be talked
into things easily.
>> JERRI: Yeah, that's what I'm
thinking, too.
>> AMBER: He's not real strong
in his opinion.
He-he sways a lot between what
people tell him.
>> JERRI: Colby does seem to be
the one we're focused on in
trying to ensure he's not
changing his mind.
Ah...
There he is.
Did you find a good spear?
>> COLBY: Yeah, I made a couple.
>> JERRI: Yeah?
Cool.
Colby was pretty excited about
going out hunting for a pig.
And I think it's a brilliant
idea, especially with the fires
right now, 'cause a lot of
wildlife has been flushed this
way.
Fire pretty much stopped.
It's always a possibility that
it could jump the river and come
over here.
I think it's highly unlikely
because there's no wind,
nothing.
>> COLBY: See where all the
ground's burning right there?
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> COLBY: The fire was right
there. See? It was right there.
>> JERRI: Oh!
>> COLBY: We'll walk back.
We'd love to have a hog around
here.
They're here. We've just got to
find them, and I'm not
having a whole lot of luck.
But I'm bound and determined to
put pork on the plate before I
leave this place.
I mean, they're not going to
live on the water, I don't
think.
They're going to burrow back
aways, and I mean, I don't have
a whole lot of experience with
hogs.
>> JERRI: I think Colby is
definitely separating the game
from any relationship with me.
I think it takes a strong person
to do that, quite honestly,
especially when there's
obviously, you know, some
attraction between us.
>> JERRI: Where to, cowboy?
>> COLBY: I don't know.
We'll head this way.
Who knows where the heck we're
going.
Jerri's scared.
She's worried that Keith and
Tina and I are going to join
together and mastermind a back
door move to get rid of her.
I don't want you to lose an
ounce of sleep worrying about
what Tina's thinking or doing or
anything like that.
>> JERRI: I'm not losing any
sleep.
I'm just... I just know that
she's thinking ahead.
I just want to beat her to the
draw, that's all.
>> COLBY: I'm not saying I'm
holding out on making a deal
with you to see how this thing
plays out.
I'm saying there's no sense in
even making a deal, 'cause if we
go into the merge undermanned,
it's all for naught, you know?
>> JERRI: Don't worry about it.
You know, it's not like you're
making a deal with the devil
here.
I'm a little leery of Colby, and
I can tell actually that he's
sort of distancing himself from
me a lot more.
And I like hanging out with you,
so, you know, it just makes
sense to me... to approach you
with it.
>> COLBY: I'll make you a deal.
It's me, you and Amber through
to the end.
>> JERRI: Make me a deal?
What is that?!
>> COLBY: Well, you were wanting
to strike a deal earlier.
Jerri probably wears a name tag
that says "puppet master" on it.
She loves having Amber in her
hip pocket, and Mitchell in the
same place.
I mean, I simply agreed to go
along with them just because I
thought it could get me down the
road a little better.
It's all good.
( Jerri laughs )
I want to win, and I don't
want to talk to anybody else
about loyalties.
Don't give me that crap.
I haven't trusted anyone since
day one, and anyone playing
smart should have been the same
way.
>> TINA: What about the pigs?
>> COLBY: Nothing.
>> JERRI: No luck.
>> COLBY: We didn't even see
anything.
I'm going to have to piggyback
your ass over this to keep you
dry.
>> JERRI: Oh, my gosh. Whoo!
Oh, you're all muscle.
>> COLBY: I'm going to need some
rest when I get back.
I'm gonna die.
( snoring )
>> NICK: Elisabeth?
>> ELISABETH: Yeah?
>> NICK: There's a pig in the
water.
>> ELISABETH: What?
>> NICK: There's a pig in the
water.
>> ELISABETH: A pig?
>> NICK: Yeah.
>> ELISABETH: There is a pig!
Right over there.
Oh, God, Mike's gone with the
knife.
>> MICHAEL: Why don't you guys
come and help me surround him.
You guys, I got him cornered
here.
Just keep walking around the way
you're walking.
>> NICK: Don't charge me.
>> MICHAEL: He won't.
You know, what I want you to do
is I want you to block off that
entrance there.
>> NICK: All right.
>> MICHAEL: Here he comes.
( pig snorting )
( pig squealing )
( sighing with relief )
>> NICK: We got a pig.
>> ELISABETH: What got it?
>> NICK: He killed it.
It was a gross thought, dude.
He had to, he had to...
I'm so glad Kimmi wasn't here.
>> ALICIA: Yeah. Where is she?
>> ELISABETH: If she was, she
would have died.
She would have died.
>> NICK: It was, it was...
>> ELISABETH: Brutal.
>> NICK: ...gross.
It was very gross and brutal.
>> MICHAEL: Life is just a funny
little blending of experiences,
and this is just another one.
How it will affect me at my end
of the tribe, I don't know.
It could go either way at this
point.
But if I go out, I'm going out
full.
And I'm so happy about that.
( chuckling )
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
Oh, this is like a murder scene.
>> MICHAEL: When I butcher a
deer, I use a hatchet and a
knife.
I think I need to cut the skin
more on the top now, too.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
>> ALICIA: Lots of butchering
going on in Kucha camp today.
>> JEFF V.: This is nothing like
a chicken, that's for sure.
>> ALICIA: We've reached a new
level.
>> NICK: This is the craziest
thing I've ever seen in my life.
>> MICHAEL: This is how I'm
going to show up at the immunity
challenge.
>> RODGER : Pig blood...
>> ELISABETH: Did you just put
that on your face?
>> RODGER: Yeah, he did.
>> MICHAEL: Just like that.
( Rodger cheering )
>> ELISABETH: You're crazy.
>> JEFF V.: Mike caught a pig.
He actually caught a pig.
>> KIMMI: I cannot deal with
these people.
I cannot... How big of a pig?
>> JEFF V.: It's a little one.
And there's going to be a lot of
ham and bacon and pork coming up
in here... soon.
>> KIMMI: What is wrong with you
people?!
This is sick.
We live in a sick tribe.
>> MICHAEL: These are pure,
fleshy steaks.
>> ALICIA: The fact that Mike
had the guts to go after that
pig says a lot about Mike's
character.
I can appreciate the fact that
Mike did that, you know?
And-and Mike did that for the
tribe.
Mike killed this pig for us so
we can all eat.
We're having a barbie.
>> RODGER: Mmm... that's
cooked...
>> JEFF V.: Oh, my God.
Mmm...
>> ALICIA: It's good, right?
>> MICHAEL: I feel better about
my position now that I've made
this kill.
I think my position in the tribe
has come up a few levels, and...
it's a good feeling.
>> ELISABETH: Whoa, we're going
to get strong now.
>> COLBY: A little bit of love.
"You all read the books and
crammed for the test.
So now it's the time for
survivor knows best.
Head down to the falls with your
thinking caps on.
If you lose the next challenge,
one more will be gone."
>> JERRI: First merge with equal
equal amounts of people on both
tribes.
We can't lose another immunity
challenge, so the pressure now
is even more immense than it was
before.
But the next two immunities are
crucial for us and our survival
at the merge.
>> JEFF: Take back the immunity
idol.
The immunity idol is now back up
for grabs.
So, last reward, you guys must
be eating pretty well.
>> JEFF V: We haven't really
been eating the chickens much
because yesterday we all went
out on a, uh, pig hunt and we,
uh, stalked a pig and, uh, we
put a spear right through its
heart and, uh, we've been eating
pig for about a whole day.
>> JEFF: Reaction? They caught a
pig.
>> COLBY: We'd like to have one,
too.
>> JEFF: You've been out looking
for a pig?
>> COLBY: Yeah, you bet.
>> JEFF: Well, today's
challenge-- certainly more
important than chickens or
roosters, even pork.
At the end of this challenge,
one tribe will return to camp
safe in the knowledge they're
secure for another three days.
The other tribe will head to
Tribal Council, and you will
vote another member out of your
tribe.
It's a simple question-and-
answer game.
There are six spots per tribe.
You'll start at the back and
move forward by filling in the
spots with correct answers.
Your goal: be the first tribe to
get right here on the yellow
spot and you get immunity.
All right?
Let's go.
Head down, pick the first
person.
Michael, Mitchell, come on up.
Multiple choice: it is possible
to improvise a compass by
magnetizing a needle which of
the following: A) silk; B)
cotton; c) hard wood; or D)
running water.
Show me your answers.
You both say A) silk.
That's right.
Take your first spots.
>> ALICIA: All right!
>> TINA: Good job! Good job!
>> JEFF: Elisabeth, Keith, come
on forward.
True or false: the number of
flies in Australia increased
after the arrival of Europeans?
You both say true.
True is correct.
Take your next spot.
All right, Alicia, Amber, come
on up.
In order to safely purify water,
it must be boiled for at least,
A) five minutes; B) ten minutes;
C), 15 minutes or; D) 20
minutes?
Correct answer: B) ten minutes.
Pick your spot.
( cheering and whooping )
Ogakor has a one-point lead.
Next two.
The answer is true.
Take a spot. We're even up.
( cheering )
Alicia and Jerri, back of the
line.
Colby, going against Jeff.
True.
>> Yes!
( cheering )
>> JEFF: Ogakor in the lead.
Kimmi says false, Jerri says
true.
False is right.
Kimmi, take a spot.
Alicia and Tina.
What was that little thing you
just did, Alicia?
Is that a little...
>> ALICIA: Just getting ready.
>> JEFF: Okay.
>> ALICIA: Third time's a charm,
hopefully.
>> JEFF: Of the ten most
venomous snakes in the world,
how many live here?
A) three; B) six: C) nine... or
D) ten?
Both wrong. It's nine.
See you again in a minute.
All right, Jeff, Jerri, you both
say true.
You're right. Take a spot.
Nick, Tina, you're both right.
>> NICK: All right!
>> TINA: Thank you, God!
>> JEFF: Take your spots.
( whooping )
Okay, Alicia, come on up.
And Mitchell, you'll be the tie-
breaker for Ogakor.
Here's what I'm thinking: I'm
thinking, this tie-breaker's a
little tougher on you, Alicia,
because Mitchell at least has
already answered one.
>> ALICIA: Right.
>> JEFF: He can always fall back
on that.
>> ALICIA: That's right.
>> JEFF: You haven't answered
squat.
You'll be leading the hike to
Tribal Council.
>> ALICIA: Thanks for telling
me.
Thanks for just reassuring me
like that.
>> JEFF: We're in a tie-breaker
situation.
If you both get it right, we go
again.
First person to miss, their
tribe loses, they go to Tribal
Council.
Multiple choice: Which of the
following animals have toxic
eggs which should not be
touched?
A) gowannas, b) cane toads, c)
akidnas or d) bearded dragons?
>> You both said B) cane toads.
You're both right.
Going to another question: When
building a fire, you should
never use dead wood to start the
fire, A);
B) situate your fire near a rock
slide; C) place wet rocks near
the fire; or D) use a car
battery to start the fire?
For immunity.
Mitchell says B) you should
never situate your fire near a
rock slide.
Alicia says C) you should never
place wet rocks near the fire.
C) is right.
Kucha wins.
( wild cheering )
Kucha, you get the immunity idol
back.
>> AMBER: We're feeling kind of
blah right now and we're not too
excited to make that hike again
tonight.
>> JERRI: And so we prepare once
again for the walk of shame.
>> MITCHELL: I'll have plenty to
say to the camera when I hold up
Keith's name.
He seems to be an instigator, a
few problems.
So, when he goes, it'll be a
sigh of relief for me.
>> KEITH: Jerri likes to think
that she is the leader in some
way because Amber and Mitchell,
she kind of leads them around a
little bit.
My goal tonight is to try to
step in and break all that up.
I'll offer my opinion to the
team and see what everyone
chooses.
>> COLBY: I don't think he has
any idea.
>> MITCHELL: Really?
>> TINA: He didn't take his
fleece or his jacket.
>> COLBY: This, by far, is going
to be the toughest council for
me because I don't agree with
the order in which the union
is voting.
Because the person to go tonight
is-is a huge asset and could
really, really be an asset down
the road.
>> JEFF: First I think I need to
address with you guys a fire
that is burning.
Keith, when you think about
that, that there truly is a
fire, does it hit you how real
it is out here?
>> KEITH: Absolutely.
And the fact that the fires are
burning so close, what they're
going to end up doing is pushing
things that are in the outback
towards us.
>> JEFF: What was your reaction
to the fact that Kucha bagged a
pig?
>> COLBY: I'm ticked off that we
don't have pigs yet.
I'm ticked off that I haven't
seen pigs or-or pheasants or
quail or anything of that sort,
but I'm not discouraged by that.
Why I'm upset is because I play
to win, and nothing else is
acceptable in any way.
>> JEFF: Sort of based on what
you just said, Colby, let me
make the observation of the day:
Kucha is kicking your ass, and
the question I have is: Does it
change your strategy tonight at
all in thinking about what tribe
do we need to take to this
merge?
>> TINA: That's the hardest part
about this game, because you are
pulled in so many different
directions.
You're pulled with loyalty,
you're pulled with self-
survival, you're pulled with
team survival.
And it boils down to you.
You're going to have to be the
one to make the decision.
And... it's brutal.
>> JEFF: Well, obviously,
tonight's vote is pivotal.
Behind me, three torches.
Two of the three-- Ogakor.
It's time to vote. Colby.
>> MITCHELL: Keith, you add some
tensions with the group at
times, and my hope is that by
eliminating you, we eliminate a
little bit of that friction.
>> TINA: This was not my
original intended vote.
However, on the way here to
Tribal Council, a new scheme was
developed.
So, in the spirit of the
Olympics, let the games begin.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally your
votes.
Once the votes are tallied, the
decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
First vote: Keith.
Keith.
Three votes, Keith.
Mitchell.
Three votes Keith, two votes
We have a tie.
Okay, our first tie.
Here's how it'll work: Keith,
Mitchell, you will not vote.
The other four will vote again.
Obviously, big vote for Ogakor.
I think it's only fair that I
give each of you guys a chance
to plead your case, a chance to
say to the tribe why they need
you to be to beat Kucha.
Keith?
>> KEITH: I'm a competitor and I
will fight to the bitter end to
win for this team and continue
to do the heavy work that I've
contributed with the team thus
far.
I won't give up.
>> JEFF: Mitchell, why should
they keep you?
( sharp exhale )
>> MITCHELL: We all pulled a
little fast one on me, but...
but I agree with Keith,
actually.
I want you guys to win this.
I want you guys to go on.
I want you guys to beat Kucha.
And physically, mentally,
emotionally, I'm drained.
I wanted very, very badly to go
far in this game, but if these
next few challenges are strictly
strength, Keith is stronger than
I am.
I can't compete with that.
There's no way I can compete
with that.
>> JEFF: Okay.
We'll have a revote.
You will vote for either Keith
or Mitchell.
You are voting to vote them out
of the tribe.
All rules stay the same, but you
have to vote for one of the two.
Jerri.
>> JERRI: Mitchell, I promised
you from the very beginning of
this game that I would not vote
for you, and I am staying true
to that promise.
>> TINA: This game isn't easy.
I didn't come out here to starve
myself and to face the elements
to keep the weakest person.
>> JEFF: I'll read the tie-
breaker votes.
Keith.
Mitchell.
We have another tie.
It seems we're deadlocked.
In the Survivor rules, in a
deadlock, you go to votes cast
in previous Tribal Councils.
The tribe member with the most
votes is the person voted out.
How many votes have you had cast
against you, Keith?
>> KEITH: None.
>> JEFF: Mitchell?
>> MITCHELL: One.
>> JEFF: One.
One vote is the difference.
I need you to bring me your
torch.
>> MITCHELL: Okay.
>> JEFF: It's been a long vote,
Mitchell.
The tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, I have a feeling that
tonight's Tribal Council is
going to have a monumental
effect on this tribe.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
>> JEFF: Coming up, scenes from
our next episode and Mitchell's
final words.
Next time on Survivor: Will
Ogakor continue their losing
streak?
>> COLBY: Excuses are done,
check them at the door and let's
get down to business.
It is going to be one hell of a
show today.
>> JEFF: And at Kucha, the
feathers fly.
>> ALICIA: I'm tired of you and
the ... chickens!
>> KIMMI: Excuse me? Don't wave
your finger in my face!
>> ALICIA: I will always wave my
finger at you.
You want me to say it to your
face?
>> MITCHELL: That definitely
took me by surprise.
Well, I guess the bright side
is, I get to eat, and I need to
eat.
Look at me...
I feel a little bit betrayed by
some of them, but at the same
time, I want to shake their
hands and congratulate them for
pulling the wool over my eyes
because they definitely got me.