>> JEFF: 24 days ago, 16
survivors were abandoned in
the Australian outback.
The eight remaining members of
the Barramundi tribe have now
made it past the halfway point.
Tonight, in a special episode
of highlights and never before
seen footage, we'll take a
closer look at their adventure
thus far.
>> KEL: I'm a captain in the
U.S. Army, and for them to
question my integrity over a
piece of beef jerky means a lot
to me.
>> RODGER: Maybe I've been
playing the Kentucky Joe part a
little bit too much, and maybe I
need to come out a little bit
more.
>> JEFF: Day One found 16
need to come out a little bit
more.
>> JEFF: Day One found 16
strangers abandoned in one of
the most unforgiving places
anywhere on Earth-- the
Australian outback.
As two separate tribes, Kucha
and Ogakor, they gathered
whatever supplies they could
carry, and began a five-mile
hike to find their camps.
It didn't take long for certain
personalities to clash.
>> DEBB: Nick, stay in the
front, Nick, and keep us going
north to northeast, okay?
>> NICK: Even from the
beginning, people were
automatically getting on
people's nerves.
We were walking through the
grass, and Kimmi was like I
can't stand Debb.
>> KIMMI: Debb is not even a bad
person.
She means well.
It's just she's not somebody in
the outside world I would talk
to, because she'd make me crazy.
>> DEBB: See, if we're going
southwest, how are we going to
get the dry quickbed?
>> ELISABETH: Because that's
north!
>> DEBB: That's right.
>> COLBY: You all right,
Maralyn?
That trek let me know that this
was for real.
That was a long trek we had
through deep sand, and that
fired me up, because that is the
quickest way to find out what
people are made of.
>> AMBER: This rice is very
heavy.
I really want to get there soon.
( whooping and cheering )
>> JEFF: Once the tribes had
found the flags and canoes that
marked their beaches, the mood
was upbeat.
( whooping )
But with night approaching,
Kucha and Ogakor turned to the
serious task of assessing their
living conditions.
>> DEBB: We got enough rocks
here, too.
We could build a pretty decent
shelter just using rocks.
>> MITCHELL: Colby, his luxury
item was the Texan flag, which
is great, because it covers us
and blocks us from the wind and
the sun.
>> COLBY: Don't get me wrong.
When I wake up in the morning,
there's two things I'm thankful
for.
I'm thankful I'm alive, and I'm
thankful I'm a Texan.
>> JEFF: Keith and Jerri got off
to a shaky start.
>> JERRI: No, but it's not going
to stay.
But see, we put it on the
grommet for a reason, so that
the flag wouldn't rip.
>> KEITH: You can't.
You won't be able to go through
that on a flat surface.
>> JERRI: Tension between Keith
and I...
I think him and I kind of rubbed
each other the wrong way.
>> JEFF: On the first night at
Ogakor, sleep was hard to come
by thanks to Colby.
( loud snoring )
( snoring continues )
>> MARALYN: God, has anybody
gotten any quality of sleep?
>> KEITH: Colby.
We had added a new sound to the
outback.
MARALYN: Oh, Jesus.
>> KEITH: All these critters are
going what the hell is that
animal!?
( soft laughter )
>> COLBY: I snored?
>> Trust me, you were snoring.
>> It's like you had sucked sand
into your nose.
>> Oh, man!
>> COLBY: It doesn't bother me
much, but... might explain why I
don't have a girlfriend, I don't
know.
( women groaning
sympathetically )
>> JERRI: I hate to say it, but
you're probably right.
( laughter )
>> MITCHELL: I'm a little
annoyed because I'm waiting for
Kelly to pull his stuff
together, 'cause we're going to
go fishing, but it should be a
good trip 'cause he might tell
me some things that might be
useful to any strategies that we
may have planned.
I mean, he's a nice enough guy,
but if there is one person to
vote off right now, it
definitely would be him.
>> KEL: See, there's like a rope
hanging from that limb over
there?
>> MITCHELL: All right, now I
see it.
I wonder what the other team is
planning.
>> KEL: You think they'd be
talking about that that early in
the game?
>> MITCHELL: I don't know.
>> KEL: So, we have nothing in
here?
>> MITCHELL: Do you see anybody
as the weakest yet?
>> KEL: Everybody has some very
strong strengths.
I mean, have you thought about
that?
I mean, obviously you have, to
ask it.
>> MITCHELL: Well, I think we
all have; it's kind of
inevitable.
In a few days, we're going to
have to... right?
>> KEL: You don't ever learn
anything by talking.
You learn things by listening.
Right now I'm listening to them,
I'm learning about them.
Tell me who you think is the
weakest, then.
>> MITCHELL: I don't know.
Maralyn is probably the weakest.
Part of me thinks to maybe even
go for the most threatening too,
you know?
I'm trying to decide which way
to go.
>> KEL: I think Jerri and Mitch
would look at me as someone they
would vote off because I would
be potentially dangerous to them
because I'm mentally and
physically strong.
We're good.
We can head back.
>> JEFF: Voting strategy wasn't
the only thing on the
survivors'
minds.
Fire quickly became a priority
for both tribes.
>> KIMMI: I'm angry!
Angry, angry, angry, angry,
angry, angry, angry!
We're generating some sparks.
We tried every way to get this
fire going.
Yes, I was smashing the rock,
but I made it into an energy
release, because you just can't
say to people you're a jerk-off,
shut up, so you focus your
energy somewhere else, and
you're fine.
>> AMBER: Fire.
( loud, abrasive squeaking )
>> Whoo!
( high-pitched whooping )
>> JEFF: Despite their efforts,
neither tribe succeeded in
generating more than a few
sparks and a little smoke.
>> MARALYN: Until we can get a
fire and boil water, we're not
going to be eating much of
anything.
>> JEFF: But luck was about to
change for one tribe.
The first challenge brought the
hope of fire and immunity.
Waterproof matches.
One of the things we're playing
for tonight, right here.
We're also playing for something
else-- the immunity idol.
It was Ogakor who had the first
taste of victory.
Your reward-- waterproof
matches.
( cheering )
And that night, they had their
first taste of hot food as well.
>> One vegetable paella coming
up.
>> JEFF: But professional chef
Keith didn't quite live up to
his credentials.
>> AMBER: I was pretty surprised
the first time I tasted the
rice.
I was really looking forward to
a warm meal.
And the first bite was nothing
like I imagined.
I'm not complaining, I promise,
but...
It's hard to eat.
>> JERRI: The first time Keith
made rice, the rice was way
undercooked.
I hate to say it, but it wasn't
really very good.
>> COLBY: I don't think the
first batch of rice went over
real well.
In fact, I think it went over
like a pickle in a punchbowl.
>> KEITH: Anyone want seconds?
>> JEFF: On Day Three, the
torches were lit for the first
Tribal Council.
For Kucha, there was little
question about who should be the
first person voted out of the
tribe.
>> ALICIA: She's very set in her
ways, she doesn't like to be
second guessed, and it makes it
very hard for us to deal with
her in any kind of group
dynamic.
>> NICK: At this point, I think
that Rodger would probably be
the smarter vote, but I think
that the group dynamics and
people fitting in well together
is important, and Debb is
definitely on the outside with
certain people.
>> KIMMI: She just chooses to be
independent, and she's just a
strong-willed person.
It's not a bad thing, it's just
not what I need.
>> JEFF: First person voted out
of the tribe... is Debb.
The tribe has spoken.
>> JEFF K: It's a reward.
"A leap of faith is not for the
skilled,
Just step off the edge, try not
to get killed."
>> JEFF: With Day Four came the
first reward challenge-- one
that gave Rodger something to
worry about.
>> RODGER: Today's challenge is
probably going to be jumping off
a cliff into some water.
I just basically learned to swim
right before we came out here,
plus I just never did like
heights.
( whooping )
( yelling )
>> Come on, Rodger!
>> JEFF: Though Rodger gave his
all, it wasn't enough to secure
a Kucha victory.
Ogakor crossed the finish line
first, and walked away with two
warm blankets as their reward.
>> RODGER: For five quarts of
beans, I'd have jumped off of
there again.
I think.
Well, after we came back from
the award challenge, it's right
down the river here a ways,
there's a rapids running through
there.
>> NICK: Hey, guys,
everybody in the hot tub!
♪ ♪
>> ALICIA: They have a rock bed
with all this water, just like
cascading sounds, like a little
waterfall.
Like little white rapids.
We all ran and got in.
It's just like a Jacuzzi, and
it's become Kucha Jacuzzi.
>> ELISABETH: It just felt so
good on our muscles, and I think
for the first time, all the
workaholics in our group took
like, ten minutes to just think
about the fact that we jumped
off a cliff!
>> ALICIA: Rodger!
Rodger, come on, we got a
Jacuzzi going over here!
>> RODGER: Oh, man, that's...
Whoo, that's cold!
But it feels good.
>> I think that our morale was
more positive to see that
Kentucky Joe was able to take
the swan dive off the cliff and
be like, you know what, I might
not be the best at it, but you
know what, I'm not going to let
my team down, and that is just
like a greater triumph than two
blankets.
>> RODGER: I'm losing my trunks
here!
I'm losing my trunks!
>> JEFF V.: Who would have
thought Rodger would be the
first for this?
>> MICHAEL: It's a fine line
between the physical weak link
and one of the strongest morale
builders.
We all kind of gather around him
for that father-figure type of
thing, so I'm just trying to
decide how important that's
going to be to my ultimate
survivor.
>> RODGER: Whoo!
I could sleep right here
tonight.
>> ALICIA: I know.
>> RODGER: As far as what
they've been calling me--
Kentucky Joe-- yes, I've been
kind of playing along with that.
I'm kind of playing the old dumb
farm boy, schoolteacher, dirt
poor, and maybe I've been
playing the Kentucky Joe part a
little bit too much.
And maybe I need to come out a
little bit more.
I didn't want the others to have
the impression that I'm ready to
leave, 'cause I am not.
I'm here for the duration if
that works out.
♪ ♪
>> JEFF: On Day Five, a storm
brewed at Ogakor in the form of
a blue bikini.
First Jerri muscled in on
Keith's cooking duties.
>> JERRI: There's a bunch more
things we can have than rice,
and I'm ready to start making
some of them.
>> KEITH: She wants to cook some
tortillas for breakfast, I think
it's fantastic.
Actually, it's a break for me.
No worries, mate.
>> JEFF: Then she accused Kel of
smuggling beef jerky.
>> JERRI: And I saw him put
something in his mouth, and it
was a dark brown color.
>> MITCHELL: I believe her,
actually.
>> JERRI: To think that someone
in our own tribe would be
sneaking in extra stuff,
especially food.
>> MARALYN: While Kel was up on
the hill, they rifled through
his bag.
>> TINA: There wasn't anything
in there at all, but all I was
thinking about, if I find beef
jerky in here, it's going to be
ugly.
>> KEL: How you guys doing?
You guys were talking about that
you thought I was eating beef
jerky.
It was a blade of grass.
I smushed it up into my jaw, and
I was chewing on that.
I was just chewing grass.
>> MARALYN: Nobody had any right
to go into Kel's bag.
It would be very big of us to
apologize.
>> JERRI: No.
>> MARALYN: Gee whiz, things are
heating up at our encampment.
Oh, my butt!
>> KEL: I only learned that they
went through my stuff after
Keith told me.
We took a boat ride, and he said
hey, you know what?
Those guys went through your
stuff to check to see if they
could find this magical beef
jerky.
And it's not there in my stuff.
I mean, it's not there because I
didn't bring it.
If somebody has something to say
about me, they should have had
the guts, you know, to be able
to come face to face with me and
say, what's that in your mouth,
you know?
Our bags had been checked before
we got out here.
I mean, there's no way I could
have had beef jerky after I was
swimming in the water or in my
gear or anything, or have it out
here.
>> KEITH: Any type of
relationship, you have... stress
points.
I've already had mine with
Jerri.
These individuals here aren't
trying to cohabitate for life.
They're trying to cohabitate for
a million dollars.
>> KEL: I don't disagree with
you on the fact that I want to
win every day.
I want to win all the
competitions.
I have no problem with that.
But you have to understand
that... you know, I'm a captain
in the U.S. Army, and for them
to question my integrity over a
piece of beef jerky...
Can I finish, please?
>> KEITH: Sure.
>> KEL: Over a piece of beef
jerky, means a lot to me.
As you've noticed in the last
few days, I'm a good person, and
I'm also very simple.
You know, I don't do a lot of
talking.
I'm not the life of the party.
Maybe it bothers you guys that
I'm not as talkative as you guys
are, and maybe that rubs you
guys the wrong way.
>> MARALYN: Kel, they got caught
up in this beef jerky frenzy,
and nobody had any, nobody had
any right to go through your
bag.
Your attitude about all of that
was, uh, incredibly controlled,
because if it had been me, hey,
I probably would have torn the
whole camp down!
Somebody went through my bag?
Hello!
Everybody on this whole team
considers you a valuable part of
the team.
>> KEITH: Oh, that is very true.
>> MARALYN: And we just don't
want this to rub you the wrong
way.
>> KEL: Well, look, it doesn't
rub me the wrong way, because I
don't get upset very easily, and
I can't remember the last time I
ever gotten angry.
I mean, I just don't get angry,
and I found this more comical
than anything.
I was going, who are these
people?
Why are they, where do they come
from that they just think that
this captain is going to
jeopardize his career over a
piece of beef jerky?
Either they don't like me, which
is quite possible, or they want
to sabotage my character as a
way of making me someone that's
not desirable for an alliance.
And that's too bad if they're
playing the game that way,
'cause I'm not going to play
the game that way.
I'm not going to play it dirty,
and I'm not going to bring this
issue up to them because it's
just going to develop more
confrontation.
It does bother me, but the main
aspect right now is to develop a
solid team.
>> NICK: "The next challenge may
go too far,
Just say rub-a-dub-dub, thank
God for the grub,
Close your eyes, plug your nose,
and swallow hard."
We're eating.
>> ALICIA: We're eating bugs!
>> NICK: We're eating something.
>> JEFF: On Day Six, Kimmi felt
the pressure of the second
immunity challenge.
>> KIMMI: Let me go last.
I'm a vegetarian, which means I
don't eat land-dwelling animals.
I'm not eating amphibian,
I'm not eating reptile,
I'm not eating mammal,
I'm not eating fat.
>> JEFF: But in a tie-breaker,
she pulled through by swallowing
a mangrove worm, securing
Kucha's first immunity victory.
( cheering )
At Ogakor's first Tribal
Council, Kel couldn't overcome
the stigma of being the loner,
an accused beef jerky smuggler.
The army captain was deserted by
his tribe.
>> JERRI: He made it too easy to
cast this vote too early in the
game.
>> MITCHELL: The only comfort I
have in voting this way is the
fact that you brought this on
all by yourself.
>> TINA: I know you're probably
a good military person, but
you're the person who least
likely tried to fit into our
tribe.
>> MARALYN: If you were lying in
the Simpson Desert, dying of
thirst, every single one of us
would give you a drink of water.
>> COLBY: Thanks for playing.
We have some nice parting gifts
for you.
>> JEFF: The tribe has spoken.
>> JEFF: By Day Seven, Mike was
becoming more restless about the
food situation.
>> MICHAEL: I think people are
still recovering from the
coldness of the night.
But I kind of wish everybody
would take advantage of the
early morning fishing, 'cause I
think we could get a lot of
fish.
We were going to have seven
poles in the water this morning.
Maybe they're just relying on me
to bring in the fish.
I do know that bringing home
food does secure me longevity in
the tribe, which is an equal
incentive to go out and get fish
as my yearning for food.
>> JEFF: By Day Eight, Maralyn
was feeling secure with at least
one of her friendships.
>> MARALYN: Tina is a fabulous
woman.
She is a star.
I trust Tina the most.
>> TINA: Maralyn and I have
bonded more so than I have with
any of the other people.
It might be our ages.
>> JEFF: But at the immunity
challenge, it was Maralyn
stumbling that robbed Ogakor of
a victory...
>> Kucha!
>> JEFF: ...sending them back to
Tribal Council, where Maralyn
again asserted her bond with
Tina.
>> MARALYN: I'm conjoined with
>> JEFF: But she learned the
hard way that at least in this
game, friendships aren't always
worth a million dollars.
>> TINA: Mad Dog, I love you.
I value your friendship more
than anything.
This vote has everything to do
with the promise I made, has
nothing to do with you.
I hope you'll understand.
>> MITCHELL: It kills me to do
this to you.
It was difficult to watch you
get all scraped up in those
challenges.
>> JERRI: Fireside concerts will
not be the same without you.
>> COLBY: The last nine days
have really taken their toll on
you, both physically and
emotionally.
>> JEFF: The tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
( indistinct chatter )
>> JEFF: On day ten, Mike
continued to obsess over fish.
Every last bit of them.
>> MICHAEL: Livers and kidneys,
these are hearts.
And these are...
I'm not sure what those purple
things are.
Those are probably the pancreas
or something.
I don't know.
And this is...
I don't know what this stuff is,
but it was just in one of them.
I scaled these puppies, too.
We're having fish skins today.
These are the fish eggs.
I ate the stomach, and I ate the
heart, the liver, and, uh, I
think the pancreas.
And...
>> JEFF V.: He's crazy.
>> At least he's cooking it now.
>> MICHAEL: Um, these are just
the leftover...
The leftover...
( laughs )
At least I'm cooking it now.
>> He used to eat it raw.
>> MICHAEL: And we had eyeballs
last night.
Or two nights ago.
>> NICK: Mike eats fish guts,
but Mike eats things that just
aren't necessary.
Why eat a fish eyeball?
It has zero nutritional value
as far as I know.
>> MICHAEL: The only part of the
fish that we haven't eaten at
this point is the actual outer
core of the head, the skull.
>> KIMMI: Let me just clear that
up.
Mike eats just about everything.
Mike ate the eyeballs, Mike ate
the pancreas, the liver, the
kidney, the intestine, the
stomach.
>> I don't care.
>> I like the intestines, but...
>> KIMMI: Not all of us are
eating that.
He's the only one that ate
eyeballs.
>> JEFF: And when Mike went out
to catch more fish, Jeff got
annoyed.
>> JEFF V.: Mike bumped me out
of the boat to go fishing.
It wasn't right, and I wanted to
go off on him right then and
there.
But then I thought, no.
How can I use this situation to
my advantage in garnishing
respect from the tribe?
Which is exactly what I did.
>> KIMMI: Jeff?
I'll take you fishing later.
>> JEFF V.: It's okay.
>> KIMMI: So, you didn't say
anything?
>> JEFF V.: No.
I don't care.
>> KIMMI: All right.
>> JEFF V.: They can catch fish,
they can catch them.
>> ALICIA: Everybody should get
a turn.
This is not, first person awake
gets in the boat.
Wake somebody up and say, "I'm
going fishing.
Did you want to come?"
That's so easy to do.
If Jeff said no, then it's on
him.
But, no, right away the decision
is made, Mike is up, he's going.
And they just got in the boat
and left.
That cannot happen.
It just can't happen.
>> NICK: Say something to him
then.
>> ALICIA: This is...
This is a group, people.
>> NICK: Then say something to
him.
>> ALICIA: I will say something.
>> NICK: Just let it be?
>> ALICIA: 'Cause things have to
be fair, you know?
It can't be like that.
>> JEFF V.: Alicia was, like,
"Well, fine.
If he wants to do it that way,
we're voting him out."
There it is on a silver platter.
Conflict.
I'm in the middle of it, but it
doesn't look like I'm in the
middle of it.
That's the way I hope things
sort of play out.
( animals chittering )
♪ ♪
>> JEFF: On day ten, Kucha was
back in action.
They won three chickens and a
rooster at the reward
challenge...
( indistinct chatter )
>> ALL: Yay!
>> JEFF: ...much to Kimmi's
dismay.
>> KIMMI: Wait, don't break her
wings off.
>> RODGER: She ain't gonna...
Who's next?
>> KIMMI: Can't they give us
some edamame, some tofu?
( Nick laughs )
>> JEFF: And just when Kucha
seemed to have it all, Michael
made good on his promise to
bring in more food.
On day 11 he killed a wild pig.
( pig squeals )
>> JEFF V: Mike killed a pig,
and there's going to be a lot of
ham, bacon and pork coming up in
here.
>> KIMMI: What is wrong with you
people?
This is sick.
I live in a sick tribe.
>> ALICIA: It's good, right?
>> JEFF V.: Mmm.
>> ELISABETH: Whoa.
We're going to get strong now.
>> JEFF: That night at Ogakor
there was no banquet, just more
rice.
>> MITCHELL: Damn, that was
good.
>> ...That's not gonna happen.
>> TINA: Should we play our game
now before everybody gets
sleepy?
>> JEFF: With morale low, they
decided to try something new.
>> MITCHELL: After supper,
Tina-- she started the idea that
since we were all feeling down,
since we were all having a
negative attitude toward each
other that we should, uh, go
around and say good things about
each other, say positive things.
>> KEITH: Jerri.
Jerri, Jerri, Jerri, Jerri.
Well, we've had our differences.
And we probably always will.
And but from get-go, it was
rough, it was rough.
And, uh, rightfully so.
I mean, we're thrown into
something to play a game.
But in a different place and a
different time, it would be much
different.
>> JERRI: Thanks, Keith.
>> TINA: Very honest, Keith.
>> JERRI: We still have Keith to
go here.
All right?
>> COLBY: Yup, that's right.
>> JERRI: I'm going to go first.
It's-It's hard, because I can be
a little bit of a control freak.
And I know that.
But, I'm...
I mean, I...
If I in any way have...
hurt your feelings or... any of
that, I'm truly sorry.
I don't have a problem saying
I'm sorry.
That was something I just felt I
wanted to do.
'Cause if I...
I didn't want to hurt anybody's
feelings, I didn't want to step
on anybody's toes, and I felt
such a great sense of relief
after that.
Well, I-I definitely feel
better, expressing this, 'cause
holding it in just sucks.
It really does.
>> KEITH: Her apologizing to me
was just enormous, and, uh, we
were able to wipe the slate
clean.
>> JERRI: I'm very glad that
I've gotten to know you, Keith,
and I...
You know what?
Some day, I-I really want to
taste your cooking.
>> KEITH: Man, you know it, and
you're going to.
If I got to shove it down your
throat...
>> JERRI: No, you don't have to.
>> KEITH: ...piece by piece, I'm
going to feed it to you.
( laughter )
>> TINA: Jerri, I'm real
impressed with you saying, you
know, saying that you were
sorry.
Sorry is a very hard word to
say.
Jerri was on my last nerve, and
just her expressing to the
tribe, I know I have these
controlling issues, made all the
difference in the world to me.
>> Well, don't we all feel
better after this?
>> ALL: Yeah.
>> I do.
>> AMBER: I like this game.
( laughter )
>> JEFF: On day 12, Kucha
continued their hot streak by
winning another immunity
challenge.
C is right!
Kucha wins...
( cheering )
So Ogakor went back to Tribal
Council for the third
consecutive time.
And though there was a plan to
oust Keith, it was Mitchell who
was taken by surprise when some
members changed their strategy
at the last minute.
>> COLBY: Man, you know this is
nothing personal.
But I'm here to win.
>> TINA: Let the games begin.
>> KEITH: And when I get to New
York, I'm buying the champagne
for dinner, buddy.
>> MITCHELL: You add some
tension to the group at times,
and my hope is that by
eliminating you, we eliminate a
little bit of that friction.
>> JERRI: Two days ago this
would have been much easier than
it is right now.
I'm very glad we buried the
hatchet.
>> JEFF: Two rounds of voting
resulted in a tie between Keith
and Mitchell.
In the Survivor rules, in a
deadlock, you go to votes cast
in previous Tribal Councils.
Tribe member with the most votes
is the person voted out.
How many votes have you had cast
against you Keith?
>> KEITH: None.
>> JEFF: Mitchell?
>> MITCHELL: One.
>> JEFF: One vote is the
difference.
The tribe has spoken.
Having lost three members in a
row, Ogakor was in a downward
spiral.
( thunder rumbling )
Things didn't get any better on
day 13.
Friction developed between Colby
and Jerri when they had to build
a stretcher for the reward
challenge.
>> COLBY: I think it's great.
I'm saying instead of starting
it over the top, start it
underneath.
>> From underneath.
>> COLBY: See what I'm saying?
>> I've got two pieces.
>> JERRI: No, I don't see what
you're saying.
God... bless America.
This...
>> JERRI: Does Colby seem like
he's in kind of a bad mood?
>> AMBER: Yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> AMBER: I don't know if one of
us said something, I mean, I
said something.
I don't know.
>> JERRI: Dudes are weird.
( laughs )
>> AMBER: I mean, he did seem
pretty stressed.
Maybe he's just, like, "You
know, I just want to be by
myself for a little bit."
>> JERRI: There's...
We have no reason to be
stressed.
We built a... awesome stretcher.
And I want to help make him feel
better if I can.
This whole thing is stressful
enough without adding more
stress.
( indistinct chatter )
>> JEFF: For the fourth time in
a row, Kucha came through with
another victory.
( cheering )
And Ogakor reached a new low.
>> AMBER: I'm so tired of
losing.
>> Don't let 'em break your
spirit...
>> JEFF: Although Kucha was a
well-oiled machine at the
challenges, there was hostility
back at camp.
Alicia and Kimmi clashed over
the chickens.
>> KIMMI: What the hell is up
your butt!?
>> ALICIA: Do not yell at me
about the chickens.
>> KIMMI: I am not getting...
>> ALICIA: But don't jump all
over me, sweetheart!
>> KIMMI: I'm not getting upset.
>> ALICIA: Don't ever...
>> KIMMI: Don't wave your finger
in my face and mumble under your
breath.
>> ALICIA: I will always wave my
finger...
>> KIMMI: If you have something,
yes.
>> ALICIA: You want me to say it
to your face?
>> KIMMI: Yes, say it to my
face.
>> ALICIA: Yes, I will be happy
to, I'm saying to your face
right now!
>> KIMMI: Thank you.
>> ALICIA: I'm tired of you and
the ( bleep ) chickens!
( indistinct chatter )
>> AMBER: "Just keep your wits,
and you'll make it with ease,
the prize is the idol, and
that's much better than cheese."
>> JEFF: When the note arrived
for the next immunity challenge,
Ogakor decided to take charge of
their desperate situation.
>> COLBY: It is going to take
every ounce of-of keenness, of
smarts, of strength, of
everything we have.
The excuses are done.
Check them at the door and
let's-let's get down to
business.
It is going to be one hell of a
show today, and it's...
You know, I think we're as ready
as we're going to be.
Come on!
( indistinct chatter )
>> JEFF: The pep talk worked.
Ogakor made a sterling comeback
at the maze challenge.
>> TINA: Yeah!
>> COLBY: Come on, go, go, go!
( screaming )
>> AMBER: Oh, yes! Whoo!
( crackling thunder )
>> JEFF: Kucha was finally
forced to return to Tribal
Council.
>> ALICIA: She and I have not
got along from the beginning.
The whole food thing is really
becoming an issue.
It separates her from the rest
of the tribe.
>> NICK: This could be a nasty
game, but you have to play with
class.
>> ELISABETH: For a strong
Kucha, it's the best vote.
>> JEFF V.: You're a great girl,
and I look forward to the banana
split on the other side with
you.
>> JEFF: The tribe and Mother
Nature has spoken.
Kimmi took the fall for the
disharmony at Camp Kucha.
With the merge of the two tribes
now just around the corner,
Kucha still had a one-member
advantage over Ogakor, the
importance of which was not lost
on the tribe mates.
>> NICK: We're really hoping to
go in to the merger six to four,
and that way, we could just
basically pick them off one by
one.
>> JEFF: But before the next
immunity challenge could take
place, tragedy struck the Kucha
tribe.
( Michael screaming )
>> ELISABETH: In the water.
>> NICK: You okay?
( indistinct chatter )
( Michael groans )
>> Oh, my God!
>> NICK: He's burned.
He's burned pretty bad...
>> ELISABETH: Here's some water.
>> NICK: Give him water.
>> JEFF: Michael passed out and
fell into the fire, severely
burning his hands.
>> NICK: Stay in the water.
Stay in the water.
>> ELISABETH: Do you want me to
come in with you, Mike, and swim
with you?
>> MICHAEL: Look at these
things.
>> ELISABETH: Oh.
>> NICK: Oh, Mike.
>> ELISABETH: Keep your hands in
the water.
>> NICK: Oh, my God.
>> Mike, I'll have you lie down
there, Mike.
We're gonna get you home.
( Michael screaming )
>> See you, Mike.
>> COLBY: Bye, buddy.
>> RODGER: Hang in there, buddy.
>> MICHAEL: Bye-bye.
I love you guys.
You guys do what's right.
You guys know what to do.
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: His evacuation left
Kucha and Ogakor with five
members each.
The field had unexpectedly been
leveled for the upcoming merge.
>> JEFF: On day 19, the merge
was put into motion when tree
mail arrived for the two tribes.
>> AMBER: "Boys night out.
You've wondered for weeks what's
their camp like, so here's your
big chance.
Send your scouts for the hike.
The men will go visit while the
women remain.
Cook a big dinner.
There will be guests to
entertain."
So, we'll stay here.
The guys are going to come to
our camp.
We'll cook dinner for them.
They're going to cook dinner for
you guys.
>> COLBY: I better iron a shirt!
>> Oh!
( Colby laughs )
>> ELISABETH & ALICIA: "Girls
night out.
The women will go visit while
the fellows remain.
Cook a big dinner.
There will be guests to
entertain."
>> JEFF V.: So you guys are
going over there, and those
girls are coming over here.
They're keeping the chicks
apart.
>> JEFF: The survivors believed
they were sending scouts to
assess the livability of each
other's camps and decide on a
home for their new tribe.
>> TINA: Fee fi fo food, I smell
the blood of a Kucha tribe.
>> ALICIA: What's up?
>> TINA: Hey.
>> ELISABETH: Hi.
>> JEFF: But Ogakor was
expecting the men of Kucha.
>> ALICIA: Can I tell you how
funny this is?
The guys were expecting you
guys.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah.
>> JERRI: No!
>> We have all the...
>> KEITH: Anybody home?
>> JEFF: And Kucha was expecting
the women of Ogakor.
>> JEFF V.: What?
>> What's up, fellas?
>> How you doing, Nick?
>> NICK: Good.
>> JEFF V.: So, your note said
what, boys night out?
>> KEITH: Boys night out.
>> COLBY: Boys night out.
>> JEFF V.: Ours said girls
night out.
>> RODGER: Ours said girls night
out.
We were expecting the women over
here.
>> COLBY: Rodger, I'm real
sorry, bro.
I didn't even bring a skirt with
me, so I can't do anything for
ya.
( laughter )
>> JEFF: During the visit, Jeff
felt there were too many cooks
in Kucha's kitchen.
>> KEITH: ...Roasted.
You pop 'em right out.
Now eat like candy.
It's like the tenderloin of
chicken.
>> JEFF V.: We knew Keith had
brought some type of big pan
for his luxury item.
And we knew that he was somewhat
of an arrogant little, whatever,
and so he comes over, and he
immediately starts futzing with
the pan.
>> KEITH: You want things to
boil over.
>> JEFF V.: You do?
>> KEITH: Yup.
>> JEFF V.: You know, it's what
we expected.
I just hate that Alicia's not
here, because I think he
probably annoyed her most.
( laughs )
>> JEFF: Back at Ogakor, the
girls fantasized about food.
>> JERRI: Hot fudge.
>> ALICIA: I'm, like, craving a
hot dog and...
>> TINA: Cashews and pistachios.
>> AMBER: We're torturing
ourselves.
We are absolutely torturing
>> ALICIA: Have you ever had
different flavored Tootsie
Rolls, like cherry Tootsie Rolls
and...?
>> JERRI: Yes.
>> ALICIA: And vanilla.
>> JERRI: Vanilla?
>> ALICIA: They are yummy.
>> JEFF: On day 20, everyone
agreed-- Kucha camp was the
place to live.
>> JERRI: They have a kitchen,
they have all these wonderful
things.
I am so stoked about going to
their camp.
>> TINA: We've got mail!
>> JERRI: Whoo!
>> JEFF: But the survivors were
thrown for a loop when a tree
mail note told them to start
from scratch on a new beach.
>> ELISABETH: Anxious.
>> TINA: "You have just 15
minutes to get all your work
done.
Hike back to the crock swim.
The map shows you the way.
Take all that you can, but the
canoe's got to stay."
>> AMBER: Oh!
>> JERRI: We were ready to pack
up and move to Camp Kucha.
Roll up the flag inside.
And when we looked at the map,
it was a completely different
spot.
Maybe they're doing the same
thing, and we're going to have a
whole new camp.
>> AMBER: Yup, I think that's
what it is.
>> JEFF V.: Damn it!
>> Things are never easy around
here.
>> RODGER: We were a little
angry about it...
>> COLBY: Six minutes.
>> KEITH: I was really
frustrated with it.
I just didn't want to leave
there.
Just...
You know, we were there, we were
comfortable.
It was a real pain.
>> RODGER: Let's go.
>> JEFF: The ten remaining
survivors reunited and named
their new tribe Barramundi.
They then toasted their merge.
>> ALL: Yay!
( cheering )
>> ALICIA: You know, it was
really kind of interesting,
because in the middle of all
this celebrating, this game is
still being played.
Every minute of every day.
>> JEFF: Alicia was right.
The first immunity challenge for
Barramundi proved, old tribes
die hard.
After lasting ten hours in an
endurance contest, Keith, who
had prior votes stacked against
him, asked Tina to let him have
immunity.
>> KEITH: Hey, Tina?
>> TINA: Hey, what?
>> KEITH: I need this.
>> TINA: I looked over at Keith,
and Keith said, "Tina, I need
this one."
He must have really thought that
he was going to get the votes
cast against him.
It's the hardest thing I've ever
done to come in.
>> KEITH: Yeah!
>> JEFF: With the immunity
talisman around his neck, Keith
was protected from the voting at
Tribal Council.
It was just the advantage the
old Ogakor tribe needed.
>> JERRI: We learned early on in
the game that you had one vote
against you previously.
>> COLBY: It was a, uh,
strategic move that was
determined the first week we
were here.
>> JEFF: After another double
tie, this time between Jeff and
Colby, Jeff's vote from a
previous Tribal Council came
back to haunt him.
Colby, how many votes have you
had cast against you?
>> COLBY: Zero.
>> JEFF: Jeff?
>> JEFF V.: One that I know of.
>> JEFF: Enough.
Jeff was the first member voted
out of the Barramundi tribe.
Jeff, the tribe has spoken.
( birds calling )
By day 22, the remaining members
of the old Kucha tribe decided
it was time to fight back.
>> RODGER: You know we're just
sitting ducks now.
>> ALICIA: You know what?
>> RODGER: Sitting ducks sitting
by the fire.
>> ALICIA: It's not fun anymore.
Laying down and talking to
everybody at night is not as
much fun as it used to be.
>> ELISABETH: We're not here to
sit back and wait for someone to
vote you off.
I just really would love to just
light a fire under everyone.
Well, that makes me sick.
I'm not going to sit here and be
a sitting duck.
If no one else wants to keep
playing, I'll do whatever it
takes to stay out here longest
and keep... keep Kucha going.
>> JEFF: Elisabeth led the fight
by taking shots at the weak
links in the Ogakor alliance.
>> ELISABETH: I think there's a
crack in their tribe right now.
Pay attention to Jerri and Tina,
because I think Jerri and Tina
have issues.
>> TINA: I try to stay away from
cooking so I don't have to be
judged.
>> JERRI: Ah!
>> ALICIA: Elisabeth, although
she comes across as a very meek
and mild kind of person, she is
a serious competitor, believe
me.
Elisabeth is a force to be
reckoned with.
See, look at them.
>> JEFF: Elisabeth's hunch about
the wavering Ogakor alliance
wasn't farfetched.
Even Colby was ready to sever
all ties with Jerri.
>> JERRI: Um, have you ever
considered leading Keith and
Tina to believe that you want
the three of them to be the
final three?
Maybe...
>> COLBY: Oh, they're fully
convinced that's what's going to
happen.
>> JERRI: Oh, they are?
>> COLBY: I mean, they...
I was painted into a corner
and-and had to lie to her to
convince her that there wasn't
anything going wrong.
I didn't like the fact that I
had to lie, but because I was
lying to Jerri, I didn't lose
sleep over it.
>> JEFF: On day 24, Keith won
his second consecutive immunity
challenge, assuring once again
he could not be voted out of the
tribe.
Again!
( applause and cheering )
Congratulations.
But at Tribal Council,
Elisabeth's efforts to get Jerri
voted out fell short.
The fragile Ogakor alliance
held.
>> AMBER: Girl, you're strong
inside and out, and, uh, that's
the main reason why I have to
vote for you, because you're
threatening.
>> JERRI: Not only do you
intimidate the hell out of the
women around here, but also the
men.
They are scared to death of you.
>> KEITH: This is just strictly
part of the game, and it's part
of our process.
>> JEFF: Final vote...
Alicia was the eighth member to
go.
Alicia, the tribe has spoken.
But she will return as the first
member of the jury that
ultimately decides which of the
final two tribe members will be
the sole survivor.
The remaining members of
Barramundi must now carefully
consider their voting
strategies, because old tribal
loyalties are now less important
than the good will of this new
jury.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
Go!
The winner of the reward
challenge is flown to an exotic
location.
And tribal loyalties start to
unravel.
>> COLBY: We're talking about a
lot of money at stake.
>> KEITH: No, I understand that.
I understand that.
Kucha tribe's in a great
position, because we are going
to sacrifice one of our Ogakor
members.
>> ALICIA: Whoo!
>> ALICIA & KIMMI: Get it, get
it, get it! Get it!
It's right there!
>> KIMMI: Right there!
>> ALICIA: It's right there.
Get him, get him.
>> KIMMI: What is it?
>> ALICIA: You got him!
You got him.
>> KIMMI: What is it?
>> ALICIA: Whoo! What is it?
Can we eat it?
>> JEFF V.: It's a prawn.
>> KIMMI: It's a prawn. Yay!
We need a bigger bucket.
>> ALICIA: We need bigger...
We need a pot.
What do you want me to do?
>> KIMMI: Here.
>> JEFF V.: Take it.
( Alicia mumbles )
( Jeff V. laughs )
>> ALICIA: Oh!
>> KIMMI: Oh, no!
>> ALICIA: No!