>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Sparks flew between Kimmi and
Alicia.
>> KIMMI: Don't wave your finger
in my face.
>> ALICIA: I will always wave my
finger...
>> KIMMI: What have I said about
the chickens, though, nothing!
>> ALICIA: I'm tired of and you
the ( bleep ) chickens!
( bird squawks )
>> JEFF: Ogakor had their own
problems-- they kept losing
challenges.
>> AMBER: I'm so tired of
losing.
>> JEFF: But a pep talk from
Colby fired up the troops.
>> COLBY: It is going to take
every ounce of strength.
It is going to be one hell of a
show today.
>> JEFF: Survivors ready!
Go!
>> Get it.
>> Where is it? Here it is.
>> JEFF: After a long losing
streak, Ogakor rebounded and
regained the immunity idol.
>> TINA: We're out.
( screaming happily )
>> JEFF: So Kucha made the hike
to Tribal Council.
Next vote, Kimmi.
The tribe has spoken.
Eleven remain.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( thunder crashing )
>> ALICIA: Wow, you guys.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God.
Did we find the matches?
( thunder crashing, rain
pouring )
>> RODGER: The rain, yes.
We got to Tribal Council last
night, hadn't been there
probably five minutes, I guess,
and then all of a sudden, here
comes... the heaviest rain we've
had since we've been here.
I mean, it really came down.
Put our fire out.
So then we had to use one of our
matches to light a candle in our
hut.
Got the candles going and
searched through and found the
very warmest, well, not the
warmest, but really the driest
clothes that we had.
A lot of us had wore our clothes
to Tribal Council that we'd been
used to sleeping in.
I know I did, for one.
That was a mistake.
( thunder crashing )
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God!
This is crazy.
Is that coming in from the
outside?
>> JEFF V.: Yeah, I think it is.
>> ELISABETH: Oh!
>> JEFF V.: Oh, my God.
It's coming in hard.
This is going to suck.
>> ELISABETH: When it rains
here, it means you're cold at
night, you don't sleep.
Rain is... I mean, it puts you
in such an extreme disadvantage.
It's... it takes you a day to
recover from rain.
I mean, there's a risk of
getting sick, you're sleeping in
the cold, wet.
There's nothing worse than the
rain here.
( thunder crashing )
Nothing worse.
'Cause being cold is guaranteed
at night.
But cold and wet?
Stick a fork in me.
It stinks.
>> JEFF V.: Good night, Jim Bob.
( scattered chuckling )
>> ALICIA ( chuckles ): Shut up.
"Jim Bob."
( thunder crashing, rain
pouring )
>> JEFF V.: I love this place.
You gotta love it.
( thunder echoing )
>> MICHAEL: It's amazing how you
can live off the land, eight
city people can come out here
and live off the land.
It's amazing.
Not only food wise, but shelter
wise and safety wise, and, um,
heat wise.
And starting a fire this morning
with wet wood.
It's just amazing to me.
It's a whole... my outlook on
life has changed 180 degrees.
And I'm this kind of guy.
I'm this kind... you know, this
should be nothing for me.
But, uh, I am a changed man
already, after 16 days.
Very changed.
And if I last another 16 days,
who knows what's going to happen
to me.
>> ALICIA: Today is day 16.
We are thinking ahead now to,
uh, the merger.
We have four more days until
that happens.
>> JEFF V.: We started with 16
people.
Six people are voted out of the
outback.
Then when it gets to ten people,
everybody comes together into
one tribe and the game, all of a
sudden, becomes every man for
himself.
>> NICK: There's one more
immunity challenge left, we have
six and they have five, and, uh,
that's a huge advantage because
the pressure is on them to win
the next challenge, and, uh,
we're really hoping to go into
the merger six to four, and that
way we could basically pick them
off one by one.
>> JEFF V.: We are a very cocky
group.
It's fun to beat them and make
fun of it.
It's fun to have them talk about
how hungry they are, and us go
in there and win all their food.
That's fun!
>> AMBER: Oh, my God, I'm so
hungry.
>> JERRI: There's enough in here
for...
>> AMBER: I'd say three
tortillas.
>> JERRI: Yeah, I could get
three tortillas out of that, but
I'd say we go two.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
( Jerri laughs softly )
And to think the other tribe is
eating eggs.
>> JERRI: Bastards.
And soup, and spices.
>> AMBER: And chicken, and pig.
>> JERRI: I just, at some point,
have to get my hands on some
chocolate.
I fear I might go psycho.
And I'm not kidding.
I had a discussion with Colby
regarding chocolate and how
chocolate releases the same
endorphins that sex does, and
since none of us are having sex,
that that's probably why we keep
reverting to the chocolate
discussions.
I'm going to bathe myself in
chocolate.
>> AMBER: I can't get over... I
just want to bite into one of
those so bad, it's unbelievable.
Like a peppermint patty.
>> JERRI: Right now, I can
actually, in my wildest fantasy,
picture pouring hot chocolate
all over...
some hot dude's bod and having
sex while licking it off at the
same time.
That's like my ultimate fantasy
right now.
>> AMBER: It's like when you
pull apart the chocolate...
( Jerri squeals in frustration )
( Amber laughs softly )
>> COLBY: When you're asleep at
night in the tent, and you hear
moaning and groaning about
Hershey Kisses, you know
what's really going on though.
It ain't about the chocolate.
>> JERRI: Vanilla ice cream...
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
>> JERRI: ...with hot fudge
trickled all over the top!
>> AMBER: Yes!
( both scream happily )
>> COLBY: She's using her
thoughts of chocolate to
substitute for her thoughts of
sex.
It's just making for a very
uncomfortable camping trip.
>> AMBER: Peppermint Pattie!
>> JERRI: I think Colby's
afraid of me.
Because this fantasy I have
about chocolate and sex
definitely involves him.
Oh, God, I can't take.
I can't take it anymore!
>> COLBY: I may be a lot of
things, but I ain't no Hershey
bar.
( laughing )
>> JERRI: Snickers!
>> AMBER: Kit Kat, Milky Way,
M&Ms!
Reese's Cup!
A meatball sub!
>> JERRI: Oh, yeah!
I love those!
>> COLBY: This is ridiculous
man.
They're driving me nuts.
( girls yelling, bongo playing )
Bring on... get rid of
these goons, and let's get
something going.
This is crazy.
( Jerri laughing )
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
>> COLBY: Hey, girls, guess
what's for dinner?
( Jerri laughs )
>> BOTH: Rice.
>> COLBY: We're having white
rice.
( both moan )
( bongo plays )
( chicken clucks softly )
>> ELISABETH: Chicken feed, huh?
>> RODGER: I really don't think
there's a thing in there that
will hurt you.
>> ELISABETH: I think it would
probably be better cooked, we
know it's clean... after I eat a
handful.
I just wonder if it's been,
like, stepped on and stuff by
other chickens, and...
>> RODGER: Well, if it's
cooked...
>> ALICIA: That's good,
actually.
>> ELISABETH: Actually, not bad.
( Michael speaks indistinctly )
>> ALICIA: Chicken feed.
We bring back the chicken, the
rooster, the chicken feed, and
of course, in true Kucha style,
we're trying to figure out how
we can utilize every single
little thing we brought back.
Elisabeth and I said, "Can we
eat that?"
Because it just looks like nuts
and grains and corn and wheat,
and, you know, it just looks so
good to us for some reason.
And he told us, you know, he's
like, "Yeah, it's good for you."
>> MICHAEL: Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Yeow.
You guys, it's popping.
You guys should see this stuff.
It's popping like popcorn.
You guys, come here quick.
It is popcorn!
It's popcorn!
It's cracking, it's popping.
>> ALICIA: Can you believe that?
It is popcorn.
It's popcorn.
There's popcorn in this pan.
This camp just gets better and
better every minute.
>> MICHAEL: Ow! Wow!
Ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
>> JEFF V.: I don't know about
this chicken pop feed, whatever.
I just... I don't know.
It's good, and I hated it, the
whole thought of eating chicken
feed just made me sick.
But the more I eat it, the
better it gets.
>> ALICIA: Do you love it?
>> JEFF V.: Oh, my God.
>> ALICIA: That just, we--
forget it.
We are now addicted.
It's so good.
>> MICHAEL: Oh, my gosh.
>> ALICIA: And we have, like,
chicken popcorn.
We wake up in the morning, we
make it.
After we eat breakfast, in the
afternoon, we make it.
( thunder crashing )
At night, we make it.
And we're going to find out,
like, somewhere down the road
that, like, something was in it,
and we're going to have like
eight nipples and laying eggs,
and I don't know, but until that
happens, I'm going to keep
eating it because it's so good.
It's so good.
>> MICHAEL: Let's kill those
chickens so they don't eat any
more feed.
( Michael laughing )
( chicken clucking )
>> KEITH: Jerri and Amber went
to pick some tomatoes.
Jerri has, um, decided she wants
to do fried green tomatoes, but
they're cherry tomato.
>> JERRI: But I can tantalize
our taste buds with fried green
tomatoes this evening.
>> AMBER: Getting creative.
>> JERRI: Have to.
>> COLBY: Thank you.
>> JERRI: They aren't quite as
ripe, but...
>> KEITH: You don't do fried
green tomatoes with cherry
tomatoes.
My thought was maybe leave them
on the vine just another couple
days, they'll be nice and bright
red and real juicy and good to
eat.
Another day, those would have
been perfect.
But, uh, doesn't look like
that's going to happen.
>> JERRI: Well, it just would
help if you weren't quite so
pessimistic about ideas that
others have other than your own.
>> KEITH: I wasn't pessimistic.
I'm not picking on you about
you tomatoes.
>> JERRI: You already did on the
way here.
You said, "I don't think that
can be done."
>> KEITH: That's good, well,
then this will be good.
We have fried green tomatoes.
>> COLBY: Keith and Jerri, are
just... like two alley cats
scratching with each other.
They're fighting over fried
green tomatoes of all things,
and it's ridiculous that the
rest of us have to sit through
all this.
>> JERRI: I don't... yeah, I
think it's done yet, Keith.
It looks totally soupy.
It needs to sit there till it's
dry.
It's going to be soupy.
>> COLBY: Keith is a chef,
man.
You don't have to insult the guy
by telling him he doesn't know
what he's talking about.
I think it's disrespectful and
rude.
And that's what Jerri loves to
do, because she knows it's going
to ruffle his feathers.
>> JERRI: You got to let the
rice sit.
>> KEITH: You can't.
...sticking to the bottom and
burning.
>> COLBY: It's all breaking up,
though.
>> JERRI: It's 'cause he kept
stirring it.
You've got to leave it in there.
>> TINA: Stop it!
Both of you!
Or you're going to time out.
I'm not their mother.
It's not my position to get in
the middle and send them both to
time out.
But to be honest, I think one of
the problems needs to go.
We can't afford for people not
to get along.
Jerri makes me feel
uncomfortable.
You know, you're always walking
on eggshells around her.
And it's just no fun living in
that type of situation.
>> KEITH: Another...?
>> COLBY: Oh, yeah!
They're kind of like okra.
They really are kind of like...
>> AMBER: Did you try one?
You didn't like it?
>> TINA: It has a sour... almost
a sour bite to it.
>> JERRI: It's 'cause they're
green.
( Jerri chuckles )
>> KEITH: So the fried green
tomatoes sucked.
I knew they would.
Poor Colby stomached all of
them, including mine, told her
they were great.
'Cause Colby is a gentleman.
But I do not like them.
>> AMBER: What will the reward
be today?
>> JERRI: I don't know.
I'm feeling good about it today,
though.
"The next challenge you face is
no walk in the park.
Now we'll find out who's afraid
of the dark!
To lead the whole tribe there
can only be one.
The winners will picnic and the
losers get none!"
A picnic!
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
Like a barbecue!
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
( Jerri screams happily )
Yeah!
Oh, my God!
>> KEITH: This better be good.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> COLBY: Peanut butter and
jelly sandwiches.
>> JERRI: A picnic!
Food!
Can you imagine, like, real
food!
>> AMBER: Sandwiches.
>> JERRI: I can't, oh...
You know there's going to be
dessert.
Tina!
>> TINA: ...and there's food
involved.
>> JERRI: Yes, there is.
>> AMBER: A huge at of food!
>> JERRI: "The winners will
picnic and the losers get none!"
>> AMBER: Picnic. A picnic.
>> JERRI: Picnic.
>> TINA: And I am not afraid of
the dark, sister.
( whooping )
>> JEFF V.: I have really good,
uh, vision.
>> ELISABETH: If it's in the
water, we're afraid of the dark.
>> ALICIA: We don't want to be
in the dark.
We're not eat leading... we're
not leading the tribe.
>> ELISABETH: I'll follow.
>> ALICIA: Me, too.
>> MICHAEL: "The winners
will..."
>> JEFF V.: Picnic.
>> ALICIA: Picnic, honey.
>> NICK: We just got you're tree
mail for tonight's reward
challenge.
It sounds like we're going to be
doing something at night, almost
definitely, um, and it says "to
lead the whole tribe there can
only be one."
Um, so it sounds like one person
will be leading the tribe
through the dark.
You're good, you're good, you're
good.
Okay, toward my voice, toward
my voice, toward my voice.
>> ALICIA: We don't want the
opposition to win the picnic,
because we have a big immunity
challenge tomorrow and, uh, if
they win, it could... it could
give them that little boost, uh,
and we don't want them to have
that.
>> NICK: Towards my voice,
towards my voice.
>> JERRI: Definitely.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God, a picnic
is so much better...
>> JERRI: There's no mess.
No plucking, no cutting.
>> AMBER: It's already made for
us.
>> JERRI: Oh, a bottle of
chardonnay.
A little cheese and crackers.
>> NICK: Uphill a little bit.
Right, right.
To your right a little bit.
Right, straight, straight.
>> JERRI: Put your hands above
your heads, interlacing your
fingers, pointing to the sky.
If Kucha wins this is reward, it
would suck!
( laughs )
They don't deserve it.
They've been eating like kings
over there, and I think it would
be really nice of them if they
threw this one for us.
>> AMBER: Picnic, picnic,
picnic, picnic...
>> JERRI: Ah... picnic!
>> COLBY: Dinner.
It's all about the grub.
>> JERRI: That's right.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
How goes it?
>> ALICIA: Good.
>> JEFF: Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> JERRI: Yeah!
>> AMBER: Yes, yes.
>> JEFF: Give you a little
sample.
One Doritos chip for each tribe.
>> AMBER: Oh! Doritos!
>> TINA: Oh, my gosh.
A Doritos!
>> AMBER: You can have first
bite.
>> ALICIA: Oh, my God.
Take a bite.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
Wow!
>> JEFF: One chip and one sip.
( Jerri squeals happily )
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
Something besides water.
>> JERRI: Do the Dew.
>> JEFF: A little Mountain Dew.
>> JERRI: Do the Dew, baby!
>> ELISABETH: Wow.
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: That will get you guys
going.
>> ALICIA: You the man.
>> JERRI: Unbelievable!
>> AMBER: Oh, my God.
It's so good.
>> JEFF: Certainly you guys have
figured out to survive out here
you have to be able to trust
each other, to a certain degree
anyway.
Each tribe will select one set
of eyes.
That will be your tribe's
leader.
The rest of the tribe will be
blindfolded.
And it's your leader's
communication skills that are
going to be the name of this
game.
Sitting atop two elevated
perches and using only your
voices, the two chosen leaders--
Jerri for Ogakor, Nick for
Kucha-- you're going to navigate
your blind tribes through a
series of tasks.
The first tribe to complete all
the tasks wins the reward.
Here's how the course works:
First task involves two logs
and a sawhorse.
You need to get the logs into
the sawhorse.
Your next task: Get to this
table, take this trap, switch it
for the other trap that's in the
water.
When you've completed that,
you'll see a series of buckets.
Each member needs to get a
bucket, go to the water tower,
fill their bucket with water.
Once it's full, guide them to
the wine barrel, have them dump
their water into the wine
barrel.
When the wine barrel overflows,
you move to the final task.
That is getting the picnic
basket to the finish table.
First tribe to get their basket
on the table wins the reward.
Survivors ready!
Go!
>> NICK: Okay, stay there.
Stay there.
Hold hands and walk straight.
Walk straight.
Stop, stop, stop.
Bend down, bend down...
There's two logs.
No, Mike, stay.
Mike, back up.
There's a log, Jeff, you've got
a...
>> JERRI: Tina, keep going
straight.
Keep going straight.
Stop! Stop!
Amber, keep to your left.
Towards me, towards me.
Keith and Amber, come forward.
The other way.
>> NICK: Walk straight, Alicia.
There you go.
No, no, okay, stop.
>> JERRI: There's a log by your
leg, Colby, you're going to pick
it up, pick it up.
There's a sawhorse to your
left, a sawhorse to your left.
You're going to put it on the
sawhorse at both ends.
Amber, Keith, Amber, Keith, go
back, go back.
>> NICK: There you go, there you
go, there you go.
You got one.
Okay, Elisabeth stay there,
there you go.
There you go.
There, stop, drop it, drop it.
>> JERRI: Colby, go the other
side of the sawhorse, go the
other side.
Climb over it if you have to.
There's another log.
You're going to do the same
exact thing.
>> NICK: Okay, walk forward,
walk forward, walk forward.
There you go, there you go...
Walk, two more steps.
Stop, stop, stop.
There's a trap, just like our
fish trap.
Grab that, grab that, okay.
>> JERRI: There's a yabby trap
on the table.
>> COLBY: A what?
>> JERRI: A yabby trap.
Grab it, shuffle side step to
your right.
You're going to go in the water,
in the water, in the water is
another yabby trap.
Colby, back step.
>> NICK: One step more, one step
more, Mike and Elisabeth.
>> JERRI: It's hooked around the
flag.
Go back.
Colby, it's hooked around the
flag.
Lift it up then around.
No, no, no, the other way, the
other way.
No, Colby, down.
( Colby yells )
Colby, underneath, underneath
the rope, underneath the rope,
underneath it.
Okay.
Now shuffle, side step, side
step, Tina, to your right.
You're going to go in the water.
>> NICK: Right in front of you
is the table.
Right in front of you is the
table.
Mike, drop the trap on the
There you go, there you go.
Mike, Elisabeth, side step left.
Side step left, side step left.
Stop, stop, stop.
Forward, Jeff, three steps
forward.
Three steps forward.
Stop, stop, stop.
Take a bucket right in front of
you.
>> JERRI: Up on land, up on
land.
Go backwards, go backwards.
Yabby trap on the table.
On the table.
Set it down.
Come forward, come forward.
Colby stop, reach down.
Um, there's going to be buckets,
there are buckets in front of
you.
Right to your left.
Yeah, grab that bucket.
Tina, there's another bucket.
>> NICK: Everybody, side step
left.
>> Whose left?
( Nick and Jerri shouting )
>> JERRI: Okay, you guys, now,
both of you move forward.
Go forward. Go, go.
You can just keep going.
Keep going back, backwards,
backwards.
There's a silo back there.
There's a hook that you're going
to pull and fill your buckets
with water.
Face to your left then go.
There's a straight open shot.
Keith, go to your right.
>> COLBY: Jerri!
>> JERRI: Move to the right
of the silo.
There you go.
Right above your head, there is
a thing you're going to pull.
Right... no!
Keith and Amber, backwards,
backwards, backwards.
>> COLBY: Jerri!
>> JERRI: Keep going backwards.
Pull it, Colby, pull it.
Pull it, you'll feel water.
Fill up your bucket.
>> NICK: Side step, side step,
side step.
>> JERRI: Amber, Keith, go
straight, go straight!
You're going to feel Colby.
There's water-- fill up your
buckets.
Fill up your buckets.
>> NICK: Jeff, to your left.
Straight, your hands straight in
the air.
There you go, Jeff, grab it.
Now fill the bucket.
Fill the bucket.
>> JERRI: Colby, take your full
bucket, walk towards my voice.
Keep heading straight, straight,
straight.
You got it, you got it.
There's a thing.
Dump your thing in... dump your
water in there.
>> NICK: Stop!
>> JERRI: Dump it in, dump it
in.
>> NICK: Follow my voice.
Follow my voice.
>> JERRI: Now go backwards.
Go back to the waterfall, go.
Tina, come towards my voice.
>> NICK: Okay, bend down with
your right hand.
There's a big bucket.
A big tub.
Pour your bucket.
Pour your bucket in there.
There you go, there you go.
Okay, you guys need to do the
same thing you just did, okay?
>> JERRI: Stop, stop.
Keep going forward.
Now in front of you is a
wheelbarrow.
Dump it in, dump it in, dump it
in!
Amber, Keith, move forward, move
forward!
Okay.
Keep moving... stop, stop, stop.
>> NICK: Mike, Elisabeth, follow
my voice.
Step forward, step forward.
Mike, to your right, Mike to
your right.
Okay, okay, Mike, Mike, stop,
Mike, stop.
Okay, bend down.
You'll feel a big barrel, big
barrel to your right.
Fill it up.
>> JERRI: Grab Amber, grab
Amber!
Fill the wheelbarrow!
We got enough?
Good enough?
>> JEFF: You're good.
( Jerri screams happily )
Okay, Keith, Amber, towards me,
towards me, now.
Straight, straight.
Stop, Amber, stop.
Amber, stop.
>> NICK: Jeff, Alicia, stop,
stop, Jeff, stop.
Pour it...
There you go.
Pour, Alicia, pour.
>> JERRI: ...picnic basket,
pick it up!
Pick it up!
>> JEFF: You're good.
>> NICK: Okay, okay, drop the
buckets.
Drop the buckets.
Come my voice, quick, quick,
quick, quick.
>> JERRI: Right, right, no, no,
behind you...
Go, go, go!
Amber, stop.
Stop moving.
No, stop.
Rotate to your right, rotate to
your right.
All right, stop.
Forward, forward, forward,
forward.
Tina... Amber, behind you!
Amber, behind you!
>> JEFF: Kucha!
( cheering )
>> JEFF V.: Awesome!
Awesome!
( cheering )
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God, you
guys!
( cheering )
>> RODGER: Y'all have no idea
how close that was.
>> ALICIA: Yes!
( whooping, laughing )
>> JERRI: Thank you, thank you.
I needed that.
( birds twittering )
( Keith sighs )
>> TINA: Everybody here knows
the importance of winning today.
Everybody.
It is a have-to-win day.
But that's pressure.
>> AMBER: If we lose the
challenge today, that means we
will be down four to six.
The other tribe will probably
just pick us off one by one.
>> COLBY: If we don't pull this
thing off today, I don't think
it's over at all.
It seems to be the attitude of
everyone to just lay down and
die if we don't pull this thing
off.
I'm certainly not going to just
sit around and wait to be picked
off by Kucha once we merge.
That's not happening with this
kid.
>> JERRI: There's a weird
tension in the camp right now.
Colby wants to just think about
nothing but the game, and then
Amber and Tina are braiding each
other's hair and talking about
college days.
>> AMBER: And it's funny because
in my sophomore year...
>> JERRI: Everybody was kind of
chitchatting and being very
lighthearted, and I needed to
get more centered and focused.
>> KEITH: It was around my head,
it catches the back...
>> JERRI: So I knew that I
needed to get away from camp.
>> KEITH: And go like this and
it all like, whoosh, and now
it's dark out, and I'm all
tangled in this line and...
>> COLBY: Everyone was kind of
going in their different
directions, and I decided just
to come upstream, and think
about the game.
You have to be a lot more
selfish when you merge, because
at that point it is all about
getting yourself as far as you
can go.
You can't help but think about
what's around the corner.
>> JERRI: Everyone else in the
camp is looking at it as if, if
we lose today, that's it, we're
all going to be sitting ducks,
or we're going to get picked
off one by one.
I see it almost as an
opportunity to, uh, finagle my
way into the other tribe a bit
and mix things up, and freak
some people out.
If they're going to pick us off
one by one, I'm at least going
to cause a big ruckus going
down.
I'm going to wreak a little
havoc.
>> MICHAEL: Four bites, two
fish, that's it.
They died in the tin just as
fast as they died anywhere else.
I don't think I put enough water
in it.
I put enough to cover their
backs, but... I don't know if it
got too hot.
It was hot out there. Ooh.
>> ALICIA: It is hot.
>> NICK: I say we eat Doritos
and popcorn as a snack and then
have the fish and rice as a
dinner.
( animals chittering )
( Michael screaming )
>> NICK: You okay?
( Michael groans in pain )
>> ALICIA: Oh, my God.
>> NICK: He's burnt.
He's burnt pretty bad...
>> ELISABETH: Here's some water.
>> JEFF V.: What happened?
>> NICK: He passed out in the
fire.
>> JEFF V.: Passed out and fell
in the fire.
>> ELISABETH: He passed out in
the fire.
>> NICK: Stay in the water,
stay in the water.
( birds squawking )
>> ELISABETH: Do you want me to
come in with you, Mike, and swim
with you?
>> JEFF V.: You passed out?
>> MICHAEL: I-I was blowing on
the fire and the smoke went
right in my face, and I inhaled
it, and I passed out.
( Michael groans )
Look at these things.
>> ELISABETH: Oh...
Keep your hands in the water.
>> RODGER: Oh, Mike.
Oh, my God.
>> MICHAEL: I can't decide
whether I should keep trying
to bend them or not.
>> ALICIA: No, don't, don't,
don't.
>> ELISABETH: No, no, Mike,
Mike...
>> RODGER: Hang on.
Now don't... don't get out in
the deep in case you pass out.
>> ELISABETH: Yeah, I'm just
nervous he's going to go into
shock.
( Michael groans loudly )
>> MICHAEL: They just keep... it
keeps intensifying.
>> ALICIA: I know, I know, Mike.
>> RODGER: Don't get out in the
deep, Mike.
>> MICHAEL: I'm not, I'm not.
I'm on my knees.
Oh, they're stiffening up.
>> ELISABETH: You're good.
Okay, Mike, they're coming right
now.
>> ALICIA: They're coming right
Just leave yourself right where
you are.
>> ELISABETH: They're going to
put stuff on there, Mike, you're
gonna feel good.
They'll wrap it up for you.
>> JEFF V.: Hang on, Mike.
>> ELISABETH: You're good,
you're good.
Stay strong, Mike.
Stay strong.
( Michael moaning )
>> RODGER: His hands are bad.
>> ELISABETH: Stay strong.
>> RODGER: Don't go out any
deeper than what you are.
Stay right there where you're
at.
( Michael moaning )
( Michael panting )
>> ELISABETH: Okay.
( speaking indistinctly )
( Michael groans loudly )
>> ALICIA: The medics are on the
way.
They're going to look at...
>> MICHAEL: Ah, I'm okay.
( groans loudly )
( Michael moaning )
( Michael yelling )
>> ALICIA: Just relax.
Don't even look at them.
It's just going to make you feel
worse.
>> RODGER: What, he bent over,
working on the fire?
>> NICK: No, he leaned all the
way over and then he started
shaking in the fire and jumped
out.
I thought he was having a
seizure.
>> ALICIA: ...wrap them up,
you're going to feel better.
>> RODGER: I'd keep them in the
water till they get here.
( Michael yells in pain )
( indistinct conversations )
( Michael yells )
>> Keep 'em in.
>> MICHAEL: Whoo... that was
painful.
>> ALICIA: Watch out, there's a
rock...
>> MICHAEL: You guys just tell
me what to do.
On the face, on the face.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I'm good, I'm good.
>> ALICIA: He's right there,
he's right there.
You feel him?
( Michael groans )
>> MICHAEL: Man, I messed up
bad, buddy.
>> MEDIC 1: What did you do?
>> MICHAEL: I got a big
inhalation of smoke, and I
passed out in the fire.
>> MEDIC 1: Okay, well...
>> MICHAEL: You can shoot me,
you can... shots, drugs, pain...
If-if I don't... I can take it.
I'll take whatever you give me.
I'll take the pain without
drugs.
I'll do whatever you guys say.
>> ELISABETH: They're going to
give you a shot right now, baby.
>> MICHAEL: I don't care.
If it's good, it's good.
You just do it.
>> MEDIC: It's an anesthetic,
okay?
>> MICHAEL: Okay. Breathe...
>> MEDIC 1: When you breathe it
in and breathe it out...
>> MICHAEL: Okay.
>> ...it'll calm you down...
>> MICHAEL: Through my-through
my mouth only?
>> MEDIC 1: Through your mouth.
>> MEDIC 2: In and out through
the same pipe, Mike.
( Michael muttering )
>> MEDIC 1: I think we'll try
and move him to the shoulder as
soon as we can.
( all talking at once )
We're just going to bring you
out and put dressing on to
start with.
>> MEDIC 2: Mike, we're going to
do some cold dressings around
them, mate.
Just in case...
That's the way.
Excellent.
One for the other arm.
>> MEDIC 1: Put your other
arm out, other arm out.
>> RODGER: Y'all got him?
>> ALICIA: Yeah, we got him.
>> MEDIC 2: Okay, buddy.
Come on, step...
( speaking indistinctly )
Keep walking there, mate.
Keep walking.
You all right there, Mike?
( speaking indistinctly )
We got a bed up here ready...
ready to go.
( helicopter approaching )
One, two, three.
Okay, have a lay down there,
mate.
( Michael screams )
( medics speaking indistinctly )
>> MEDIC 1: Here we go.
One, two, three, down.
>> ALICIA: Hey, Mike.
>> MEDIC 1: Said he wants to be
transferred to Ogakor.
>> RODGER: Gonna switch tribes
on us, boy?
>> MICHAEL: I love you, guys!
>> ELISABETH: Love you!
>> ALICIA: Mike!
( indistinct talking )
>> MICHAEL: Where's my tribe?
>> RODGER: Calm down.
>> MICHAEL: Kucha!
>> ALICIA: Good-bye, baby.
( indistinct talking )
Bye, baby.
We love you.
>> ELISABETH: You're good.
( indistinct talking )
>> MICHAEL: Thank you...
>> RODGER: I'll keep them in
line for you, buddy.
Don't you worry about it.
( indistinct talking )
>> ALICIA: Everybody's here.
>> MICHAEL: I can't see Rodger.
>> JEFF V.: He's here.
>> RODGER: Here I am.
You thought I'd gone fishing,
didn't you?
>> MICHAEL: I can't see
Elisabeth anymore.
>> RODGER: Here's Elisabeth
right here.
>> ELISABETH: I'm right here.
>> MICHAEL: I'm looking at some
brave, beautiful people who I
have just grown to love so much.
>> ALICIA: We're all good, Mike.
Don't even worry about it.
>> ELISABETH: A-OK.
>> MICHAEL: I just want to lock
eyes with my boys and girls...
>> ALICIA: We're right here,
Mike.
>> MICHAEL: ...from Kucha.
>> ELISABETH: We'll see you
soon, buddy.
>> RODGER: Hang in there, buddy.
>> MICHAEL: I love you, guys.
>> ALICIA: Stay strong.
>> MICHAEL: You guys do what's
right.
You guys know what to do.
>> RODGER: Okay.
>> MICHAEL: You guys know what
to do.
You know exactly what to do.
ALICIA: How many fish do you
want?
>> JEFF V.: See you, Mike.
>> RODGER: Hang in there, buddy.
( helicopter blades whirring )
( helicopter engine fades )
( bird screeching )
>> JERRI: Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
>> AMBER: All right!
( Amber whooping )
>> JERRI: It's a little
disturbing.
>> KEITH: Uh-oh.
>> AMBER: Oh, no.
>> JERRI: Don't get too excited.
>> AMBER: ...tree mail.
>> JERRI: No, it's... it's a
little strange.
"There has been an accident at
the Kucha camp, and one of their
members has been evacuated.
( Amber gasps )
As a result, there will be no
immunity challenge today...
( Amber gasps )
...and all five of you will
continue to the merge.
You will receive further
instructions soon."
>> AMBER: Oh, my God!
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> AMBER: That's awful.
>> COLBY: Oh, my gosh.
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> KEITH: Hopefully, they're all
right.
>> AMBER: I wonder that this
means.
Like, I wonder if we...?
If... if they...
>> JERRI: If they have someone
hurt, they have five now, right?
>> AMBER: I hope it's not a
snakebite.
I hope it's something that heals
like... a broken... you know.
( Tina moans )
>> JERRI: I think a snakebite
might be better than a broken
something.
"Evacuated."
I mean, that's... that's hard
core.
>> ELISABETH: It was... it was
so strange to sit there, and
we're all smiling at him, and
he's cracking jokes and it was
so hard, 'cause the minute, you
know, the minute he was out of
sight, it was like decompress
and just, like, oh, gosh, that
just happened.
And it just really hit hard.
Because it makes you... makes
you realize that...
you're out here for a period of
time with a group of people, and
you're doing everything
together, and, you know, you win
games, you lose games, you know,
you're sleeping in the same
quarters, and one of your
teammates goes down, and for him
to ask to see each of us.
I mean, I know at one point he
was like, "Wait, I can't see
Elisabeth."
And I'm... I was, like, behind
someone.
I'm like, "I'm right here, Mike.
You know, here I am."
And his eyes were just locked on
ours, locked.
>> RODGER: We're going to either
go win this thing or lose this
thing as a team, I think.
I don't think there's... unless
somebody jumps boat on us in
mid... in the middle of the
stream, which is possible.
Uh, we're either going to stick
together as a team, and, uh,
possibly Mike's accident, uh,
might have brought some of them
to the realization that, you
know, maybe there's other things
more important than even the
million dollars, you know.
>> JEFF V.: This merge is going
to be intense.
Ogakor will be relieved.
I think, that they'll... I mean,
I think they're good people, and
I think that they're going to
feel bad, and sincerely have
compassion for us and for Mike.
But they weren't part of that,
they didn't experience it.
They didn't... hear it.
And so that feeling of, oh, my
goodness, it's going to have to
be very quickly replaced with
relief.
That we're merging together,
'cause we had them.
We had them.
They had to have been scared.
They had to have been afraid.
There's no way we were losing
this challenge today, no way.
And, um, we're going to... we're
going to kill 'em.
We're going to eat 'em up and
spit 'em out, and that's the way
Mike would want it to be.
It was the last thing he said
to us before he left, and it's
exactly what we're going to do.
( fire crackling )
>> RODGER: God, we give thee
thanks today for this beautiful
Lord's day and for all thy many
wonderful blessings.
We thank thee, dear Lord, for
this food, which Mike caught for
us today, and we pray dear Lord
that you will be with him as he
undergoes surgery.
We pray that you will be with
the doctors.
Give them the knowledge and the
experience and the wisdom to fix
his hands so that they will be
once again returned to normal.
We just pray that you will be
with him, be with his family,
and we just ask that you would
bless them and give them
strength.
And we would ask, dear Lord,
that you would also bless the
ones remaining here in this
group, and ask that you would be
with us and give us your
guidance and also your strength
and your support.
In your son's holy name we ask
it. Amen.
>> ELISABETH: Amen.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode and hear
what Michael has to say.
Next time on Survivor:
>> JERRI: We're moving!
>> JEFF: Due to Michael's
accident, Kucha and Ogakor will
merge with five members each.
>> JEFF V.: Damn it.
>> JEFF: Is it a time of
celebration...
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: ...or do tribal
loyalties run deep?
>> JEFF V.: I saw Colby walk
over to Keith, and they're,
like, pointing at us and
counting fingers, like, "She's
going to go first" and "He's
going to go second."
We weren't together 15 minutes
and it started.
>> MICHAEL: You don't... you
don't want to leave.
The longer you're here, the
longer you want to stay here.
And it's not even about winning
as much as... playing.
The winning will be
anticlimactic.
The playing is where it is for
me.