>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Three days before the merge,
Kucha had a one-member advantage
over Ogakor.
>> NICK: It's a huge advantage,
because the pressure is on them
to win the next challenge.
>> JEFF: And it looked like they
might regain their winning
streak when Nick led them to
victory in the reward challenge.
>> NICK: We are a very cocky
group.
It's fun to have them talk about
how hungry they are, and us
going there and win all their
food.
>> JEFF: Ogakor couldn't hide
their frustration.
>> JERRI: The other tribe will
probably just pick us off one by
one.
>> JEFF: But before the immunity
challenge could take place, the
game took a violent twist,
Michael passed out in the fire,
and was severely burned.
>> ( Michael groaning )
>> MICHAEL: Kucha, you guys
know what to do.
>> JERRI: There has been an
accident at the Kucha camp, and
one of their members has been
evacuated.
>> JEFF: Michael's evacuation
leaves Kucha and Ogakor even,
with five members each.
Tonight, will new strategies and
new friendships be born as the
two tribes merge into one?
Who will be the first person
voted out of the new tribe?
>> They've been handed a gift.
They are going into this with an
advantage, because we were
supposed to be one up on them
anyway.
They were about to be voted off
one by one, and they know it.
>> JEFF V.: For the last three
weeks, we've been competing with
another tribe.
At this point we get down to ten
total people, and we come
together and merge into one
tribe.
>> KIMMI: It blows my mind to
even picture any sort of loyalty
toward...
I don't even know them.
We have been through so much
together.
>> JEFF V.: We've talked about
strategy and how we were going
to merge with this other team
ever since Mike got hurt,
because the last thing that he
said to us as he left was that
somebody from Kucha needs to
take this money.
And regardless of what happens,
we need to eat 'em up and spit
'em out.
>> ALICIA: This is going to have
to get ugly if we really want
this thing to work.
>> The first vote, we have to do
something to get an advantage.
>> NICK: It's going to depend on
that first vote, and it's smooth
sailing from there.
>> You hit it on the head, son.
>> ELISABETH: If I had to vote
right now, I'd vote Colby, and
I'd vote Jerri next.
>> ALICIA: It's got to be Jerri
and Colby first.
>> JEFF V.: My instinct says
Tina was the guiding force.
When I was standing in that
number one circle and I was
quizzing her, and the way she
was answering my questions just
told me that she was putting on
a face, and was a shrewd woman.
>> JEFF V.: We were just trying
to figure out who probably is
Ogakor's weak link, and maybe we
can convince them to come over
and vote on our side.
>> ALICIA: Tina will not turn on
her team.
>> JEFF V.: No, I know Tina
won't turn.
>> ALICIA: There's no way.
>> Most likely to turn is Keith.
>> Keith and Amber.
>> ALICIA: I just think Nick and
I are going to have to be ready
for anything 'cause he and I are
going to be the first ones.
>> KIMMI: See, I think they'll
be gunnin' for me.
>> JEFF V.: Listen to you all
talking.
It's me.
Plus, Kimmi on the first reward
challenge.
They asked who Debb voted for,
and Kimmi said Jeff, so they
know that I have a vote against
me.
We're anticipating a five to
five tie in the first vote.
And in the rules, when there's a
deadlock tie, the person with
the most votes accumulated to
that point is the one to leave.
>> NICK: I had totally forgotten
about that.
>> JEFF V.: It's never left my
mind.
>> RODGER: If they remember
that...
>> JEFF V.: But then again,
that's a vote against me, so it
wouldn't leave my mind.
( laughter )
>> ELISABETH: What happens then?
>> I would be, like, forget
about it.
>> COLBY: Yesterday everything
was canceled because of the
accident with Kucha.
You know, you're just left with
days that seem like there's at
least 19 to 20 hours of
daylight.
We have no idea what's going
on, and we have no idea how
drastic or serious the situation
is with Kucha.
>> TINA: It's so unfortunate.
>> COLBY: Automatically, we
assume the worst... horrible.
The worst part about this is
waiting around for information.
>> TINA: It's like getting a
phone call from the hospital,
saying, "Oh, we've got him here,
but can't tell you what's
wrong."
>> JERRI: You don't think Rodger
had a stroke or anything?
( Tina gasps dramatically )
>> TINA: Oh, my gosh.
>> COLBY: We don't know
anything.
We don't know when we're
merging, we don't know the
condition of Kucha's member
who's been in an accident.
We don't know very much at all.
>> AMBER: "Boys night out."
>> COLBY: Well?
>> AMBER: It's different.
>> AMBER: "You've wondered for
weeks 'What's their camp like?'
So, here's your big chance.
Send your scouts for the hike.
The men will visit while the
women remain.
Cook a big dinner,
there'll be guests to
entertain."
So, we'll stay here and the guys
are going to come to our camp,
we'll cook dinner for them,
they're going to cook for you
guys.
>> COLBY: Cool.
So, we get to go on a hike.
>> KEITH: I'm all over that.
>> COLBY: Yeah!
Finally get out and do
something.
I better iron a shirt!
( laughing )
Big night out on the town,
brother.
>> KEITH: Big night, you know?
( indistinct conversations )
Life is good.
>> COLBY: Life is good.
>> KEITH: The merge is when the
two teams come together to make
one team, and the game becomes
one against one instead of team
against team.
>> COLBY: Tina, you going to
catch the kids some fish
tonight?
>> TINA: I hope.
You go to one camp or the other,
and I'm not sure how that
decision is going to be made at
this point.
>> KEITH: We'll get a real great
take on the guys in their tribe,
and where things lie.
>> TINA: It's important for us
to get information right now
about who's had votes cast
against them, because it's
probably going to come down to a
tie-breaker vote.
>> COLBY: We've got to be
totally silent on who's had any
votes.
>> JERRI: Yes, we do have a lot
at stake.
If we slip anything out
regarding the voting situation,
we're done.
The only thing to break the tie
is past votes for the person who
is voted for.
If they were to vote for myself
or Keith... we'd be out.
>> ELISABETH: Hey, fellas, are
you guys ready to hear this?
We got mail.
"Girls' night out.
You've wondered for weeks
'What's their camp like?'
So here's your big chance.
Send your scouts for the hike.
The women will go visit, while
the fellows remain.
Cook a big dinner, there'll be
guests to entertain."
>> JEFF V.: So, you guys are
going over there, and those
girls are coming over here.
They're keeping the chicks
apart.
>> ELISABETH: They're going to
send their chicks here?
>> ALICIA: Oh, that's sneaky.
>> ELISABETH: That is very
sneaky.
>> ALICIA: That is very sneaky.
This is how it's going to
start-- separate the boys and
the girls.
>> JEFF V.: We knew that the
merger was going to start today.
We just weren't sure exactly
how.
So, we got this note, and our
girls are going to them, and
their chicks are coming to us,
and we're entertaining them and
swooning them and somehow
convincing them that this is the
place to live-- Kucha beach.
>> ALICIA: We know we don't want
to go over there, so they better
really pull out all the stops.
>> NICK: I think we have a
really nice camp, and nobody
really wants to move to a new
place where things are real
strange.
And it would kind of be our home
field, our home turf advantage.
>> JEFF V.: If we're responsible
for the dinner, then those girls
are eating much better than
y'all are.
>> ALICIA: Wait a minute.
( all talking )
>> ALICIA: Wait, time out.
>> ELISABETH: Women will go
visit.
>> ALICIA: Do we have the
Mountain Dew at least?
>> MEN: No!
>> ELISABETH: You have two cans
left?
>> ALICIA: You see how fast you
guys turned on us?
>> ELISABETH: We have to bring a
housewarming gift.
>> NICK: We're not turning on
you.
>> JEFF V.: Nobody's turning on
nobody.
>> RODGER: We need our own
stuff.
>> JEFF V.: We got the majority
of them over here.
>> NICK: There's more of them to
woo.
We need to woo them.
>> ELISABETH: Woo-woo-woo, "woo
them"?
>> ALICIA: You know what?
I don't like you guys anymore.
>> ELISABETH: This is why they
did this to us.
As much as it stinks that Alicia
and I aren't going to get to
join in our last chicken, we
know that it's for the
betterment of the whole group to
leave and go eat plain rice with
Keith and Colby.
He's supposedly a chef.
I don't know how much he can do
with white rice, and...
We're going to miss our Kucha
spices.
>> ALICIA: Yeah, we had a lot of
good stuff going on in our camp.
Those girls are going to be well
taken care of.
>> ELISABETH: Living large.
Whoo!
>> ALICIA: Elisabeth and I felt
really strange walking away from
camp, just us two.
It was really kind of cool,
and eventually it's going to
change this game.
It's a big open book, and we got
to write the rest of the pages
that go in it.
>> COLBY: I'm very curious as to
how they've been living the last
19 days.
With their shelter, with their
eating, you know, there's a lot
of things I want to know to see
if that's where we want to be.
>> ELISABETH: I'm excited.
I'm so curious to see what their
camp is like.
>> ALICIA: Well, that's the
thing...
And how they set it up for us.
>> TINA: Fe, fi, fo, fum!
I smell the blood of a Kucha
girl!
>> ALICIA: What's up?
>> ELISABETH: Hey!
You know how funny it is--
the guys are expecting you guys
right now.
( laughter )
>> ALICIA: We had... laying out
the tablecloth.
>> It said "Boys Night Out."
>> ALICIA: They're so ready.
They're going to die when they
see your guys.
>> TINA: We've been so worried.
>> ELISABETH: They didn't even
tell you guys what happened?
>> TINA: No, not a word.
>> ALICIA: What did your note
say?
>> AMBER: Somebody got hurt and
they would not be returning.
>> TINA: And they've been
evacuated out.
>> ELISABETH: Sit down for this
one.
>> ALICIA: Yeah, this is a, it's
a big deal.
>> ELISABETH: It was good to
hear that they were worried and
hoping everything and praying
everything was okay with Mike.
He apparently just
hyperventilated and passed out.
And all of a sudden, I see him
down and he was face-first into
the fire.
>> ALICIA: His hands were burned
off.
When his hands were in the
water, the skin was floating up
above his hand.
>> ELISABETH: They were just
red.
>> ALICIA: They put a helicopter
right on our beach and took him
away.
>> TINA: Have you heard any news
on him at all?
>> ALICIA: Yeah, he's going to
be okay.
>> TINA: Glad to know it's not
one of those things that's life-
threatening.
I felt a lot of relief.
>> ALICIA: We were crying, we
were a mess.
It was really sad.
>> ELISABETH: It was very
difficult.
>> JERRI: When we first found
out yesterday that we were
merging with all five of us,
after the accident over at
Kucha... we didn't really know
whether to celebrate or feel
bad.
>> ALICIA: Whatever takes you
out of the game takes you out of
the game.
Whether it's a snake bite or the
fire, it was part of the game.
And he is the sixth person to
leave.
>> TINA: The importance at this
point in at five and five, had a
huge impact on the other four
tribes, if we had gone in at six
and four, we would have been
picked off one by one, no doubt
about it.
We're starting off the second
half of the game on equal
ground.
It's a tie ball game, we're
going into overtime.
>> COLBY: We got to be getting
close. Look at this.
Anybody home?
>> KEITH: Knock-knock.
Hola.
>> JEFF V.: What?
Wait a minute!
>> COLBY: What are you guys
doing?
Well, we took a little trip down
the beach.
>> KEITH: Hi, man!
>> NICK: Good to see you.
>> JEFF V.: So, your note said
what, "Boys Night Out"?
>> COLBY: "Boys Night Out."
>> JEFF V.: Ours said "Girls
Night Out."
>> RODGER: We were expecting the
women over here.
>> COLBY: Rodger, I'm real
sorry, bro.
I didn't even bring a skirt with
me, so I can't do anything for
you, man.
>> COLBY: When Keith and I
showed up, they couldn't have
been more disappointed.
They were ready to wine and dine
the women of Ogakor, and Keith
and I come strolling in.
Look, you guys already had the
table set and everything.
Y'all really were expecting
the...
( all talking and laughing )
>> KEITH: Colby and I were
actually kind of hoping it was
going to be the girls cooking
for the guys.
We had a good time, great
camaraderie, kind of like
soldiers in the field that are
putting their weapons down for
awhile.
>> COLBY: Well, now, you guys
called this Camp Carnage, but it
looks like you guys are living
pretty plush around here.
Our girls, when they sent us
off, they're like, "Man, check
out their camp-- if it's
smelling and there's flies, I
don't want to move over there."
( laughter )
>> JEFF V.: All I saw from Colby
were teeth-- big smile, how's it
going, whatever.
He just seemed very cheery and
very happy, and Keith seemed
like a little puppy tailing
behind him.
We saved a chicken for you.
>> KEITH: Are you serious?
>> RODGER: Yeah, we're going to
have chicken tonight.
>> KEITH: You guys are too much.
>> JEFF V.: We got spices, too.
>> KEITH: We can roast it in
paper bark.
Wrap that whole thing in there,
put the spices on and slow roast
that.
They saved a chicken for us.
They killed their last chicken
and cooked it, which just was a
real gentleman thing to do for
us.
>> JEFF V.: You know, there's a
Survivor twist to everything,
and they got us again.
I was expecting women, you know.
We were going to lather them up
and go pick them flowers, and
now we're going to have to shift
gears.
( laughing )
They're nice, you know?
They're nice guys.
I knew they would be, but I get
the feeling that Keith is an
outsider.
So far, they're exactly what I
expected.
They seem to have a good
relationship together, which I
didn't expect.
I figured that Keith would sort
of be off on his own, and he
could be, you know?
They may be working us here.
Just pick one up, take a bite,
pass it.
>> COLBY: I didn't think I'd see
chicken across these lips for 24
days.
That lemon pepper is the bomb.
>> JEFF V.: It was good chicken,
and it was good to be able to
provide them with chicken,
'cause they obviously had not
been eating.
>> KEITH: Colby, what do you
want me to do with this bone,
man?
I don't like the way we're
passing.
Can we change the passing
around?
Can we go the other way?
That was a huge thing for us.
We really enjoyed that a lot.
I think as the days go on, this
game is going to be difficult.
It is for me personally, 'cause
I get caught up in the
friendship thing quite easily.
>> RODGER: Even though it was
little tough, that was still a
good chicken.
>> KEITH: Yeah.
>> COLBY: It was an excellent
chicken.
>> RODGER: I know everybody is
nicey-nicey now, but I imagine
that'll change.
I think it will be even more
interesting once all ten of us,
the women and everybody is in
the hut.
There'll be some times I'm sure
when things won't be so nice
around here.
>> ELISABETH: You need some
help?
>> JERRI: I think I'll be all
right.
I'm just trying to cover this,
'cause you know what I just
realized?
Our only matches are in Keith's
pocket.
>> ALICIA: Uh-oh.
>> JERRI: Yeah, "uh-oh" is
right.
So, I'm thinking we should
probably cook everything because
Keith has the matches.
>> ALICIA: Are you sure he has
them?
>> JERRI: I know he does.
>> ALICIA: He's probably
laughing right now, going "Guess
what?
It's raining and I got the
matches."
>> JERRI: He doesn't realize it,
I'm sure.
I don't want to talk about Keith
in front of our guests.
>> ALICIA: Smell that.
>> JERRI: If I voice my opinions
about how I really feel about
him, they are going to figure
out that votes have been placed
against him.
He should not be in charge of
the matches.
Could have potentially now been
an issue where we couldn't eat.
>> TINA: I don't think it was a
deliberate thing where he said,
"I'm going to take my matches
with me so the girls won't have
it."
He would not do that under any
circumstances.
It's in Jerri's best interest to
not to show a real hateful side.
Jerri's a good chick.
>> JERRI: Normally it looks a
lots better than it is right
now.
>> ELISABETH: We're going home.
( laughter )
>> JERRI: We decided that I was
going to make my famous
tortilla, and we opened a can of
whole peeled tomatoes.
>> ALICIA: We just want to tell
you guys that your guys are
getting chicken right now.
>> AMBER: Oh!
There's no way they saved any
for us.
>> ALICIA: They're getting
chicken right now.
>> AMBER: I'm sorry we don't
have any chicken.
>> ALICIA: That's okay.
>> AMBER: This is definitely
difficult for us.
I mean, we wish we had so much
more to offer them.
It's upsetting that we can't
give them as much as they can
give us.
>> ALICIA: Wow, that looks
amazing, though.
>> JERRI: Give me, like, some
ingredients that I can get
creative with.
>> ALICIA: When you don't have a
lot of food and you open up a
can, that's like... that's big-
time.
So, we're really honored that
they did that.
>> AMBER: Watch it, it's hot.
>> ALICIA: I feel like I can't
wait to get them back to our
camp to give them something to
eat, you know?
And I never thought that I would
feel that way.
I really thought I would be
thinking I'm not sharing
anything with them.
I don't eat meat, I don't eat
pork, and I'm, like, craving a
hot dog and a hamburger; I could
care less right now.
>> JERRI: I would love a hot
dog.
( laughing )
>> ALICIA: Out of 20 hours of
being here, we've talked about
food 19 of those 20.
So, what's your favorite kind of
food?
>> JERRI: Hot fudge.
>> TINA: How about Dove
chocolate?
( everyone groaning )
>> ELISABETH: We're torturing
ourselves.
We are absolutely torturing
>> ALICIA: Have you ever had
different flavor Tootsie Rolls,
like cherry Tootsie Rolls?
>> TINA: Yes.
>> JERRI: Vanilla?
>> ALICIA: They are yummy.
>> JERRI: When did they come out
with vanilla Tootsie Rolls?
>> AMBER: I asked Alicia about
their firewood situation.
She said they have so, so much,
they don't worry about the
firewood at all.
>> JERRI: They have a kitchen,
they have all these wonderful
things.
We have nothing.
>> AMBER: I agree.
I'm totally for going.
>> JERRI: I'm so stoked about
going to their camp.
>> TINA: We've got mail!
>> JERRI: Is there chocolate in
it?
>> TINA: No, ma'am.
>> ELISABETH: Peanut butter in
that mailbox?
>> TINA: "Once you were enemies
but now you'll be one.
You have just 15 minutes to get
all your work done.
Hike back to the croc swim.
The map shows you the way.
Take all that you can, but the
canoe's got to stay."
>> AMBER: Oh!
JERRI: In the black bag, you
guys.
>> TINA: We're moving!
>> JERRI: We were ready to pack
up and move to camp Kucha.
Roll up the flag inside.
>> TINA: The other black glove?
>> AMBER: Do we need our fishing
poles?
>> JERRI: When we looked at the
map, it was a completely
different spot.
>> AMBER: Maybe they're doing
same thing, and we're going to
have a whole new camp.
>> ELISABETH: I thought about
that.
Yep, I think that's what it is.
>> JERRI: A spot that was
untouched, where we would have
to build everything again from
scratch.
>> NICK: "Hike back to the croc
swim.
The map shows the way.
Take all that you can, but the
canoe's got to stay."
>> JEFF V.: It's a good two-hour
walk. Damn it.
>> KEITH: Make sure you bring
your matches.
Mine are... I got my matches.
Nothing's ever easy around here.
>> RODGER: We were a little
angry about it.
>> COLBY: Six minutes.
>> KEITH: I was really
frustrated with it.
I just didn't want to leave
there.
We were there, we were
comfortable.
>> COLBY: I was liking that
Kucha corn.
>> KEITH: Yeah, I'm liking our
camp.
>> COLBY: Yeah, I was liking
y'all's camp, too.
>> KEITH: It was a real pain.
>> RODGER: Let's go.
>> ELISABETH: I see it, I see
it!
>> Are you serious?
( women cheering and ululating )
>> ELISABETH: We missed you
guys!
>> JEFF V.: Hey, baby.
>> ELISABETH: How are you?
>> AMBER: Guys, check this out!
Look!
Oh, my God, it's ours!
( indistinct conversations )
>> RODGER: They're doing all the
work.
I'm glad.
>> AMBER: You ready, guys?
>> JEFF V.: I'm thinking there
might be food in here.
>> ALL: Oh!
>> JEFF V: It looks like a
little picnic.
( everybody talking )
>> ALICIA: Okay.
>> AMBER: "Building a new home
is now up to you,
but before you get started, you
have two things to do.
A flag must be made once your
tribe's named.
Here's a toast to your efforts,
and the second half of the
game!"
( everybody talking and
laughing )
>> ALICIA: One, two, three.
>> TINA: Wow!
We get to make a new flag.
( everybody squealing
and cheering )
>> NICK: We opened the box, and
people just start diving their
hands in, which pissed me off,
because I was thinking let's at
least make sure we're getting
equal amounts, but Jerri and
Amber and Elisabeth and Alicia
just start yapping and
screaming, and I was like, I had
to back up.
>> ELISABETH: Oh, cheese,
cheese, cheese!
>> TINA: I've never had wine in
my life, and I'm fixin' to have
some.
( laughter )
I may get drunk.
>> Hey, guys, here's a
tablecloth.
>> This is a party!
>> JERRI: I swear, I haven't
been that excited since I was
little, and so just completely
overwhelmed with the fact that
you've been starving, and the
fact that you're in the middle
of nowhere, and there's this
spread in front of you.
>> ALL: Yeah!
( cheering )
>> TINA: It's nice starting all
over, starting on equal ground,
and it was important to listen
more than you talk, find out
what you're up against.
>> AMBER: Oh, you guys, this is
so great!
>> ALICIA: You know, it was
really kind of interesting,
because in the middle of all
this celebrating, this game is
still being played, every minute
of every day.
>> JERRI: My stomach's going
what is going on?
>> ALICIA: I have a little bit
of shock happening right now.
>> JEFF V.: They seem to be very
nice, and I thought it was all
legitimate, and then I saw Colby
and Jerri sort of sneak off and
whispering, and then I saw Colby
walk over to Keith, and then
they start whispering, and
they're, like, pointing at us
and counting fingers, like she's
going to go first and he's going
to go second, and it started.
We weren't together 15 minutes,
and it started.
( crickets chirping )
♪ ♪
>> RODGER: Thank God it's not
raining...
We need to get something up over
our heads here in case it rains
tonight.
>> JERRI: Like, what's the
purpose of putting it up here?
Like, the trees, the structure?
>> RODGER: Just to have the
trees and the shade and the...
>> ALICIA: We're gonna need a
big...
>> JERRI: Well, you know what?
I have to...
I'll just express my
opinion right now.
>> RODGER: Okay.
>> JERRI: I think...
>> Wow.
>> JERRI: On the beach right
there in the shade.
( indistinct chatter )
>> RODGER: Let's-Let's go down
there and take...
>> JERRI: All right, let's look.
Yay!
( indistinct chatter )
>> COLBY: Sometimes you run into
a situation where there's too
many chiefs and not enough
Indians, so I'm just going to
stand back.
I don't want to ruffle any
feathers at this point.
>> TINA: You don't think that if
it rains, it will rain-rain
down this thing, do you?
>> RODGER: Uh, that...
>> NICK: That was one of my
thoughts.
>> RODGER: That-That was one of
my thoughts, too.
>> TINA: But we're on this high
thing.
>> NICK: Yeah.
>> TINA: And if it runs down,
it'll run down over there, won't
it?
>> RODGER: It's called a dry
creek bed.
I don't know if it's always dry
or not.
That's the question.
My idea was to originally build
the, uh, hut up in the trees
where you got some good anchors,
and then the girls said, they
would like to stay down on the
sand 'cause it sleeps better.
>> Is that...?
>> RODGER: Go down with it a
little bit.
>> RODGER: Okay, go.
>> ALICIA: Hey, Jer?
>> JERRI: Yeah.
>> ALICIA: What was that little
big fish-- what was that?
>> JERRI: All right, you know
what?
>> ELISABETH: Oh.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> ALICIA: That would be a
perfect name.
>> ELISABETH: What is that?
>> RODGER: Barramundi.
>> ALICIA: Barramundi?
>> JEFF V.: Barramundi.
>> Ooh, I like that fish.
>> ALICIA: You...
That means, like, if you catch
this fish, we'll be eating for
days.
>> JERRI: We are called the
Barramundi tribe.
It's a great name for our new
tribe, 'cause this is when
things get slippery and
sneaky, and it's hard to catch
people.
>> ELISABETH: It's the catch of
the day.
We're quite a catch.
>> KEITH: Good old honeymoon
stage is going to end quickly.
We're going to have to go into
an immunity challenge, and it's
going to be obvious that we're
kind of two teams living as one
tribe.
>> JEFF: Welcome!
I will take the immunity idol.
Barramundi, new tribe name.
New tribe, new game.
No longer playing for tribal
immunity, playing for individual
immunity.
( all responding )
>> JEFF: This is what you covet.
Wear this, you're immune from
Tribal Council.
You cannot be voted out.
Today's challenge is called "The
Perch."
There are ten wooden pillars to
stand on, one for each of you.
I'm going to warn you-- this
could be a long one.
This challenge tests both your
will and endurance.
Last one standing wins this, is
immune from the vote tonight.
Keep your eye on the talisman!
Immunity at stake.
Survivors ready... go!
>> JERRI: Anybody want to look
up at the sky and see if the sun
might peek out?
>> RODGER: I'm-I'm afraid to
look.
>> ELISABETH: Rodger's, like,
"I'm not looking."
>> RODGER: I am fixed on the
woods up there, son.
I don't look down at the water.
( laughter )
If I did, I'd be a goner.
>> JEFF V.: I'm going to try to
alphabetize the 50 states.
>> RODGER: Well, that...
>> AMBER: Isn't there a song?
>> RODGER: Arkansas.
>> JERRI: Alabama.
>> ELISABETH: Boy, things sure
have gotten fun out here.
( laughter )
>> NICK: You guys, have a good
game.
>> All right.
>> ALICIA: Bye, baby.
>> Bye.
>> Bye, Nick.
>> RODGER: Just don't get too
close to me, Nick, 'cause I'm
liable to be next.
>> NICK: I've been sick the last
couple days, and I got up there,
felt a little dizzy, knew I
wasn't going to win, and jumped
off, and got a good hour of rest
so, that made much more sense to
me than standing up on that
block and getting tired.
>> COLBY: I'll jump in right
now...
Like, if it makes you feel
better.
>> AMBER: Colby, you're jumping?
>> COLBY: Yeah.
>> Check on Nick for us.
>> AMBER: Oh, what a splash!
( applause )
>> And it...
>> I like the flip.
>> NICK: This game's gonna go
forever.
>> COLBY: It is gonna go
My strategy was to make the-the
Kucha guys mad, to convince them
that I'm the man to vote for.
If I can draw some attention
away from Keith and Jerri, who
both have several votes for
them, we really need one of
those guys to win immunity and
the other to be camouflaged.
Because if Kucha members vote
for either Jerri or Keith, we're
going down.
It's not even bothering some of
those guys out there.
It's killing me.
>> NICK: Yeah.
>> JEFF V.: I feel so good!
>> AMBER: Uh-oh.
Jeff's bringing something out,
guys.
>> ELISABETH: Is that an ice
cream cone on there?
>> JEFF V.: No, no, that's
peanut butter.
>> ELISABETH: It's not peanut
butter now.
Both you guys, shut up.
>> JEFF V.: That's peanut
butter.
>> ELISABETH: That's not.
Is it Skippy?
>> JEFF: Hey, guys.
I have a little peanut butter,
chocolate...
>> ELISABETH: Oh!
Chocolate.
>> JEFF V.: The first person off
gets it?
>> So what are you saying
exactly?
>> JEFF V.: Who gets it?
>> ELISABETH: Colby!
>> JEFF: That's a great idea.
Colby?
>> COLBY: Yeah.
>> JEFF: Nick, come here.
>> ALL ( screaming ): No!
>> That's not right.
>> ELISABETH: This is why you
keep your mouth shut.
My mom says "Elisabeth, keep
your mouth shut!"
Do I listen?
No!
>> JEFF: He's getting a big old
dip, Elisabeth.
That's pure peanut butter right
there.
Anybody decides to bail, you can
join me.
>> JERRI: This is torture!
>> RODGER: I was just waiting
for you to say those words.
>> You can get a big scoop.
>> JEFF V.: That's not enough.
>> JERRI: No, that's not enough,
Jeff.
>> JEFF V.: That's not enough,
Forget it.
>> JEFF: Okay.
It's plenty for Rodger.
>> RODGER: It ain't very good.
Stick it out.
>> COLBY: That one bite of
peanut butter was better than
any of the wine and cheese and
crackers...
>> JEFF V.: Damn it! Shut up.
>> COLBY: Come on over to the
dark side, Jeff.
>> AMBER: If you don't think you
can outstand us, then I would
go, 'cause you're not gonna get
that later.
>> JEFF V.: Not if y'all are
gonna vote me off, though.
>> He's gonna be up there...
>> COLBY: Now, see, you hear
that, Jeff?
>> JEFF V.: What?
>> COLBY: Look at these women.
They're bound and determined to
win this.
>> Oh!
>> God.
>> Oh, my God.
>> COLBY: Oh, my God.
>> JERRI: Oh, my God.
>> JEFF V.: Elisabeth...
>> ELISABETH: Is it good?
>> JEFF: No more takers?
Okay.
Four hours.
See you guys in another couple.
>> TINA: What you got there,
buddy?
>> JEFF: Here's the offer.
An ice cream.
I got a really hot chocolate.
>> AMBER: I just couldn't stand
there.
( thunder rumbling )
>> JEFF V.: Maybe they feel
vulnerable.
Maybe those are the four people
that feel the most vulnerable.
I felt vulnerable, but, you
know, I couldn't do it.
I knew I couldn't do it.
>> RODGER: Tina out there-- she
has not had anything to eat all
day long.
She-She didn't eat any breakfast
this morning, and the rest of us
all had about a little bit over
a half a cup of rice.
And I know they're getting cold,
too.
>> COLBY: These four are pretty
damn determined.
I've never seen anything like
it.
I had no idea it would last this
long.
There's no telling how long
those four are gonna stay out
there.
Another fun day for Club
Barramundi.
>> JEFF: I'll tell you, this
fire feels good right here.
Unfortunately, not enough to
heat you up.
>> ALICIA: Yeah, we know.
>> ELISABETH: Is there any
more negotiating?
>> JEFF: Maybe.
What makes you want to negotiate
now, but you didn't earlier?
>> ELISABETH: A boat ride
back... could be worth it.
>> How long you think they're
going to stay out there?
>> JEFF V.: I heard Tina say
"Nothing is bringing me down at
this point."
I bet Elisabeth goes next.
>> JEFF: Stay dry, I'll get you
in.
>> ELISABETH: It's past my
bedtime.
>> RODGER: Getting off,
Elisabeth!
( cheers )
>> ELISABETH: Good job, you
guys.
Go get 'em.
>> RODGER: You okay?
>> ELISABETH: Oh, my God,
it feels so good.
>> RODGER: We're all real proud
of you.
>> JEFF V.: I think they've been
out there over ten hours now.
I know that Alicia is concerned
she's being voted for tonight,
so I think she's going to stay.
These people are crazy.
You guys know we got to go to
Tribal Council tonight?
>> Hey, Jeff.
>> JEFF: Your faces say a lot.
Here's what I have.
Hot coffee, or hot chocolate.
>> ALICIA: And a boat ride in.
>> JEFF: And a boat ride in.
>> ALICIA: I'll take it.
I'm done.
>> JEFF: All righty.
>> KEITH: Hey, Tina?
>> TINA: What?
>> KEITH: I need this one.
>> TINA: I looked over at Keith
and Keith said "Tina, I need
this one."
In his heart he must have really
thought that he was going to get
the votes cast against him.
>> ALICIA: I'm good.
I want coffee!
( indistinct conversation )
>> ALICIA: Are you coming with
me?
>> TINA: I am.
>> ALICIA: Oh, Tina is getting
down.
>> TINA: It's the hardest thing
I've ever done to come in.
Much harder to come in than stay
out there, because I've been out
there ten hours.
I knew for our team that I
needed to make that decision.
So I stepped down and let him
have it.
>> KEITH: Yes!
>> Good work, Keith.
>> JEFF: Wear that.
>> JEFF: What a day!
>> ALICIA: What a day.
>> JEFF: You guys just finished
a marathon immunity challenge.
Come to Tribal Council, where
unfortunately, you're going to
vote the first person out of
your new tribe.
Let's talk about today's
challenge.
Nick lasted 90 minutes.
Now, at the other end of the
spectrum, Keith lasted ten
hours, 18 minutes.
You get immunity.
Tina, Alicia lasted 10 hours, 17
minutes, 55 seconds.
Alicia, I'm thinking you
obviously must not be worried,
because you were out there for a
long time and finally said
"Okay, I guess I've proved my
point."
>> ALICIA: This challenge felt
like it was going to go on
forever.
And I don't think that my
stepping off is going to change
what was going to happen tonight
anyways.
>> JEFF: Keith, when I came up
to you and handed you the
talisman, I said
"congratulations," and you
said "Tina gave that to me."
>> KEITH: I really firmly
believe that if she did not say,
"Okay, I'm done now," we'd all
still be there, we really would.
She's become like my sister, I'm
telling you, and it was
definitely a gift.
>> JEFF: What was it, Tina, that
finally made you say, okay?
>> TINA: At this point, I'm
still a team player.
Our team advancing does mean a
lot.
I know Keith needed this.
So... it's all right.
>> JEFF: Rodger, when you look
at what happened today and how
many people took a bribe sooner
or later and jumped off, do
you think everybody here is
really worried?
>> RODGER: Well, everybody but
Keith I would say, Keith is
definitely not worried, but yes
I think anyone of the other nine
of us are, has a very good
possibility of being voted off.
>> JEFF: Here's the deal.
Survive tonight's vote, you
are here till the bitter end.
You'll be part of the jury at
the very least, you may be the
final two.
If you're voted out tonight,
game is over.
You go home, and that's it.
Let's vote.
Nick, you're up.
>> COLBY: It was a strategic
move that was determined the
first week we were here.
>> RODGER: I really like the
guy, but he's from the Ogakor
tribe and they have all got to
go.
>> TINA: He seemed like a really
great guy, this is 100% a
strategic vote.
>> JEFF V.: 'Cause everything
is bigger and better in Texas...
this lone star has got to go.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> JEFF: Once the votes are
tallied, the decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
First vote, Colby.
Colby.
Jeff.
Two votes each Jeff and Colby.
Colby.
Jeff.
I'll read the last two.
One for Jeff, that's five.
Look at that, one for Colby.
We have a tie.
Okay.
In the case of a tie, here's how
it works.
Jeff, Colby, you will not vote.
The other eight of you will
vote.
And as is customary, I'm going
to give you guys a chance to
plead your case, although I
don't know who you're pleading
to, this is obviously two tribes
voting completely down tribal
lines.
Jeff, we'll start with you.
>> JEFF V.: There's nothing that
I can say, I don't think, to
change anybody's mind.
If I go home tonight I will walk
out of here with a smile on my
face, and be very proud of every
moment that I had here.
>> JEFF: Colby?
>> COLBY: I only know how to
play the game one way and that's
full tilt, and if that makes me
a threat then so be it.
But I'm here for one reason and
that's to win, and this is the
only way I know how.
>> JEFF: What we're going to do
is, we're going to vote again.
Nick, you're up first, if you
would, please.
Thanks.
>> JEFF: Same rules apply, as
with any vote once they're
tallied the decision is final.
Jeff.
Colby.
So it's very clear, old tribal
lines run very deep in this
group.
I think we could be here until
the sun comes up and nobody here
is going to change their vote.
So we're ruling this a
deadlocked vote.
Now what happens, the rules
state we go to votes cast in
previous Tribal Councils.
Whoever has more votes, Jeff or
Colby, will be voted out.
Colby, how many votes have you
had cast against you?
>> Zero.
>> JEFF: Zero. Jeff?
>> JEFF V.: One that I know of.
>> JEFF: Enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> JEFF: Jeff, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
I could be wrong, but I have a
feeling over the next few days
new friendships are going to
emerge, new voting patterns will
form.
You guys have had a long day.
You can grab your torches and
head back to camp.
I'll see you tomorrow.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode and hear
what Jeff has to say.
Next time on Survivor:
Will tribal loyalties begin to
crumble when Elisabeth
discovers a crack in Ogakor's
alliance?
>> ELISABETH: That makes me
sick.
I'm not going to sit here being
I think there's a crack in their
tribe right now.
If you want to stay here, if you
want to keep playing this game,
you better get a little more
ruthless sometimes.
>> JEFF V.: I knew this was
going to happen because of a
very large mouth of a former
tribe member at Kucha, Ogakor
knew I had that vote, and I knew
there was nothing I could do
about it.
So I'm going home and I've had
an awesome time.
This has just been the most
amazing experience I've ever had
in my entire life.