- (Jeff Probst)
Previously on Survivor...
Kim was upset that Brandon
abandoned their alliance
to join forces with Lex.
- I was set up by somebody who
I thought was my friend.
- (Probst) And Lex's motives
were in question because of his
alliance with Brandon.
- He has no loyalty to me.
He has no loyalty to Tom.
He has no loyalty to Kim.
He only has loyalty to you.
- (Probst) The African bush was
beginning to take its toll.
- Tom's got a massive boil.
I mean, it's big.
I've never seen
a boil that big.
- (Probst) Lex won immunity and
wanted to vote for Frank at
Tribal Council, but everyone
else, including Kim, joined
forces and voted Brandon
out of the tribe.
Seven are left.
Tonight,
one more will go.
- At the last Tribal Council,
we voted off Brandon, and you
know, we had been pals since our
early days in Samburu.
But you know, I felt
very betrayed by him from the
previous Tribal Council and I
didn't trust him any longer,
so I had to vote him out.
I guess it's all part of the
game, but it still tugged at my
heart a little bit.
- Tom, Ethan, Kim and I are all
still standing, and we've got an
advantage now-- we've got
everyone else outnumbered.
But they knew what I was pretty
close to Brandon--
he was a friend-- and that I'd
have a really hard time voting
for him, and I didn't
vote for him.
We're still solid, right?
We're still solid
from day one, right?
- 100%, absolutely.
- All right.
- Lex's vote, I think,
just pushed the limits
of our alliance.
It kind of redefined how tight
our bonds were.
You know, he gave
his word to Brandon,
but he gave his word to
us, also.
Lex kind of went out an his own
and covered his own ass.
- He gave his word to me,
you and Tom,
and he gave his word to
Brandon.
Why was his word just as strong
with Brandon as it was with us?
- As much as Tommy, Lex and
Ethan think that they want to go
into the finals, the three
of them, I don't really
think that they do.
I think that they're all
skeptical of each other,
and they know,
when it gets down to
crunch time, that one of them is
going to have to be voted off.
(rustling)
- What the hell was that?
(lion roaring loudly)
- Ho...
(roaring, huffing)
- Me and little Kim were on the
2:00 to 4:00 shift and out of
nowhere we just heard lots of
heavy grunting moving closer and
closer and closer.
(lion grunting)
I think the lion is probably
stalking, but I don't know why
it would make a noise if...
(roaring)
- I thought they made that
noise when they were calling
other lions to come feed.
- You might be right.
- You know what was scary, was
the fact that you had no idea
what the lion wanted.
Are they just communicating,
or is it trying to call
the other lion in
because it smells us?
(lion growling)
Yeah, he wants
to come and eat...
(loud growling)
Oh, my God.
The perimeter is closed in all
the way with the acacia bush or
thorn bushes all the way around,
but it's only maybe six feet
tall, and I'm sure a lion would
be able to get up and over it
if they wanted in.
(lion roaring loudly)
- It's close.
- I'll protect you.
- Obviously, they live right
here, and they must watch us
every day when we go for water
as we come out in the morning
and do stuff.
They are really here.
They are really,
like, right in this area.
- I still feel vulnerable.
It's not our land at all.
It's their land, and we're just
living in it for 39 days.
(roaring)
- I think it went, "Kim, Kim,
Kim, Kim, Kim, Kim."
I think I heard it say that.
- Hey, Zonyo!
- What's up, buster?
- You just wear yourself out
walking over here?
- I'm dead.
- Having been out here now for
a month, it's just starting to
catch up with us.
Everybody's started to feel more
lethargic, weaker, and it all...
It's interesting because it all
happened at the same time.
And we felt comfortable
admitting it because it was
obvious that everyone was
feeling the same way.
- Whoa.
- It feels like you're walking
under water, so your steps are
slow, your legs are a little,
like, shaky.
You don't pick your feet up as
high off the ground because you
just don't want to, so you kind
of stumble on even just little
roots this big.
- Oh, mama cat.
- Isn't that weird?
- Holy mackerel.
- Poor Kim Johnson, her legs
are really, really swollen from
her knees down.
I mean really swollen.
She can hardly lace up
her sneakers.
- You just push it with
your finger and it stays.
It's like Silly Putty
or something.
- I know.
- It's actually
almost climbing up.
Wait till it gets
to my breasts.
- Whoa!
- Look out then!
- Our bodies are starting to
show signs of trouble.
We're start to get sick.
In the last couple, three days,
we've all noticed that we're
getting thinner.
It's starting
to really show.
- Man, you've lost
a ton of weight.
- Yeah, I'd say
I've lost 40 pounds.
- 40 pounds?
Wow.
- Let's decide: do we want the
mush or do we want the gruel
this morning?
We eat two small meals a day.
I figure we're having, I don't
know, maybe a couple of hundred
calories, if that.
And we're eating, I think, just
enough to fool our bodies into
thinking that we're getting
nutrition when we really aren't.
- It's ready.
- We have maize.
It's cornmeal, basically, is
what it is, so we eat that
either in like, just, mushed-up
balls we boil in water.
And then we snack on,
like, kernels of corn.
They don't really pop,
but we kind of brown them
and burn them.
- Those are
too hard for me.
They just--
they hurt my teeth.
- Mm-hmm.
And then we make
a corn broth soup.
- I'm eating it, even though
I don't really want to.
It's just kind of a...
just a watery gruel
with some, you know,
some corn kernels in it.
- It's just so hard
to get down because...
it's like eating chalk twice
a day, and then they
put corn in it and then
you've got chalk with some corn.
- (burps)
- Lex is worried.
- He's worried because he knows
I didn't like what he done.
At the last Tribal Council,
Lex cast a vote for Frank
instead of
Brandon.
We had an alliance, me him and
Ethan, and the alliance was we'd
vote together, and Lex
jeopardized that alliance when
he voted for Frank.
- Before I came
into this thing,
I was totally
100% anti-alliance.
I wanted to do it myself
and all by myself.
But I realized that's
impossible.
- You can't do it.
- I felt betrayed.
- I don't understand why
you don't let Lex know.
- Because when he made that
agreement with Brandon,
he didn't come to me.
He didn't
come to you either.
He did it on his own.
All he was worried about
was Lex.
Now he's got to thinking
about me and you, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I know Tom's true to me and
Kim, but probably take a little
bit to get Lex
back on his good side.
- I don't know what'll happen
in the future,
but from here on out, you know,
I'll have question with Lex.
- What's up, boys?
- Hey.
- Mail?
- Can you guess the hint?
- That is such
a cool clue!
- Look here.
- Look, look.
- What's the difference between
the pig and me?
- No boil on the pig.
- That's what I said!
- "You'll need all your strength
for events down the road.
Today is a great day
for a good carbo load."
- Pasta.
- "Proteins and sugars will
give you power to burn.
So if you are clever,
these gifts you may earn."
- (Probst) All right, guys.
For today's reward challenge,
we thought we'd give you a break
on the challenge.
And just make it pure reward.
- Yay!
- (Probst) You each have a
personalized wallet.
Go ahead and open it up.
You've each got 20,000 Kenyan
shillings inside.
We're going to have
a little bit of an auction--
Survivor auction.
- Yay...
- Just so you
know in advance,
there's a pre-determined
number of items.
The auction
will end abruptly.
You can bid in 500
shilling increments.
One American U.S. dollar roughly
equivalent to 100 shillings.
It's okay to share as long
as you're pooling money.
You guys ready
for the first item?
- Yes, sir.
- (Probst) All right.
First item at the Survivor
auction: a hot cup of coffee,
some sugar and a nice big
chocolate croissant.
Anybody want to
give me 3,000 shillings?
- 3,000.
- (Probst) Lex, 3,000.
Anybody want to go 35?
- No.
- (Probst) 3,000-- once,
twice, sold to Lex.
Come on up
and take a sample.
You got a bargain.
Pay up, please.
Thank you.
- Oh, how is that?
Lex.
- Yeah, Lex.
- How is it?
- Smile, buddy, smile.
It's good to
see you smile.
- (Probst) How about cheese and
crackers, 4,000 shillings?
- Fo- 45.and.
- I'll - 6,000.grand.
- (Probst) Going once, going
twice, sold to K.J.
- Look at that.
- (Probst) That's good.
Okay, next item.
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, Lex.
- (Probst) A nice cold beer.
Why don't we start that
at 4,000 shillings?
Big Tom, you've got
to be missing beer.
- 1,000.
I'll give you 1,000.
- It started at four.
- I don't care.
I'll bid 1,000.
- (Probst) Sold to big Tom,
1,000 shillings.
- Nice! What a bargain!
Yeah!
- Chug a lug!
-- Enjoy it.s.
- How is it?
- Easy, big guy, don't drip it.
Don't spill it now.
- All right!
- I can bid better with a
little drink in me.
- That there is a sundae.
That's a lot
of chocolate syrup.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
- (Probst)
Tell me this is not
worthy of at least 6,000
shillings.
- 6,000.
- (Probst) 6,000-- Kim.
- Seven.
- (Probst) 75.
It may not get
any better than this.
- Eight.
- (Probst) 8,000 for the sundae,
to Kim.
- 85.
- (Probst) 85 to Big Tom.
- Oh, Tom.
- Ten.
- (Probst) 10 to Big Tom.
10,000 shillings to Big Tom.
- 10,500.
- (Probst) 10,500 to Kim.
- Let her have it.
- (Probst) Wait a second.
Is there a dispute?
- Is there a dispute?
- No-- 11.
- No, it's 11.
- (Probst)
11,000 to Big Tom.
- I'll have, like, nothing
left-- 11,500.
- Twelve.
- (Probst) 12,000 shillings
for the sundae.
- Oh, God,
you guys are killing me.
12,500.
- (Probst) 12,500.
- Let her have it.
I can't do her
that way.
- (Probst) Going once,
twice, sold to Kim.
- Yeah!
- I can't talk.
- Good job, Kim.
- Oh, my God.
- (Probst) How good does that
chocolate syrup look right now?
- It's so hot, you guys.
It's like...
- (Probst) What did
you pay for that?
- I don't have...
I don't care.
It doesn't matter.
- Not enough.
- I'll give you a grand
for a bite.
-- Yeah.d?
- Uh-oh.
1,500.
(laughing)
- (Probst) What if I were to
offer you a mug of pure
chocolate syrup?
5,- I'll go 5.s.
- (Probst) 5,000 for the
chocolate syrup to Ethan.
Going once, going twice.
Sold to Ethan, 5,000.
- Good buy, Ethan.
- It's hot.
- (Probst) The next item
is a mystery item.
It could be good,
it could be a gag.
We'll start it
at 7500.
- I'll go 75.
- (Probst) 7500 to Ethan.
- - Nine. 8.
- (Probst) 9,000 shillings
to Big Tom.
You guys
must think it's good.
- Ten.
- (Probst) 10,000 shillings
to Ethan
for mystery item number one.
- Yo- I'm not sure. it?
I don't want
to get gooned.
- Eleven.
- (Probst) 11,000 to K.J.
Big Tom,
you back in?
11,000 to Kim.
Going once, going twice...
- I can't look.
- (Probst) You just bought
a hell of a meal.
(all shouting, cheering)
- Fried chicken.
- Look at the cheese
on top of it, Kim!
- Fried chicken.
- Oh, Teresa,
I'm so sorry.
Don't look.
- Kim, I'll give you
seven for half.
- Fried chicken
and mashed potatoes.
- That's the best thing I've
ever had in my whole life.
- Kim, I'll give you
seven grand for half.
- I'll give you five just
for the potatoes.
- (Probst) I don't think
she's hearing any
of you guys right now.
- I don't think she
hears a thing.
- Teresa, I'll sell
you a piece of chicken.
- How much, Kim?
- Well, this cost me a lot.
4,000 for a piece of chicken.
- I'll do it for five.
- Lex will
do it for five.
- 5,500.
- I'll give you six for
that piece of chicken.
- Six for the chicken.
Do I hear seven?
- T-Bird.
Go and get yourself
that chicken.
- 6,500?
Do I hear seven?
- No, I'll hold out.
- (Probst) Teresa, what are
you holding out for?
- Fried chicken
and potatoes.
- It's here.
- That has Georgia
written all over it.
- And a bite of potatoes?
- A bite of potatoes
for 75-- 8,000
for the potatoes, two bites of
potatoes and the chicken.
- Go, Teresa, what else are you
going to buy?
- I- Okay. it.
- 8500.
- 8,00- 8,500. once.
No, no, you got 8500.
- 10 for half the potatoes
and that chicken.
That means you only paid
2,000 for it.
- Okay, 10 for half the
potatoes and the chicken.
- Do I hear 10,500?
Going once, going twice...
- Let me help you, Kim.
Sold.
- Sold to the man.
- Mmm.
- Is that delicious?
- (Probst) Next item...
should I keep it as a mystery or
tell you what it is?
- No, no.
Show it to us.
- (Probst) Okay.
- Oh, yeah!
- Go, baby, that's good.
You be the bid.
You just go.
- (Probst) That's a hoagie.
- Oh, God, and it has
provolone cheese on it.
- Teresa, bid.
- (Probst) Let's start
this at 9,000.
- 9,000.
- (Probst) 9,000 to Teresa.
Is it time
to pool money?
Get creative.
- Move along, move along.
- This auction
will not go on forever.
- Ten.
- (Probst) 10 to Big Tom.
- 10,500.
- (Probst) 10,500 to Teresa.
- 11,500.
- (Probst) 11,500.
- Splitting it?
- Twelve.
- (Probst) 12 to Big Tom.
- - 13.0.
- 13,500.
- 14,500.
- (Probst) 14 to Big Tom,
14,500, Teresa.
- (Probst- 15,500.to Teresa.
- (Probst) - 16.0 to Teresa.
- (Probs- 16,500.big Tom.
- Give me a thousand,
I'll quit bidding.
- Nope.
- You tapped out,
Big Tom?
- I've met my limit.
- (Probst) 16,500 to Teresa--
going once, twice, sold.
Come up and
have a bite, woman.
Finally, you're in
this game.
- Yay, Teresa.
- Good job, "T."
- How good is it?
- Good enough to make you want
to slap your mama.
- Let's make this
a mystery item.
Let's start the bidding
at 9,000 shillings.
- You want to split it?
- Nine.
- 9,000 to Big Tom.
Anybody else want
in on this?
Mystery item.
Sold to Big Tom
for 9,000.
Now, I did you
right last time.
- You really did.
- (Probst)
Okay, so we're even.
- All right.
- (Probst)
Take a look.
Open that baby up.
- He did me wrong.
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, I'll kill you,
after I kiss you.
- Whoo!
- Ham.
He's a Jew, and he won't
eat the ham.
He's a Jew.
- (Probst) Big Tom, wait.
Big Tom, come here.
Whoa, be careful.
I just want to
see you enjoy this.
- He won't eat the ham.
-- Thank you.
- That's all right.
- (Probst) Half that meal that
he just split with you he's not
going to eat.
- He won't eat that.
I mean I hate it
for him.
I hate it for him.
I wished he would.
- (Probst) Ethan, get down here
and take a little bite of this.
- I'll spend every penny
I got and I don't care.
Good buy, my friend.
- (Probst) Here's your syrup.
- We hit the jackpot.
- Yeah, we did.
- (Probst) My friends,
that's it.
The auction is closed.
Hope you had fun.
- I did.
I did.
- That chicken, I think
I just lost it.
I haven't been that excited
since the bow and arrow.
- I cannot believe
I had a pot of chocolate.
- That damn beer was good.
- In the food auction, you
could definitely see alliance
lines and relationship lines
that apply to the game itself.
I mean, Kim and I have been
close since the get-go.
Tom and Ethan
have been very close too.
T. Bird and Frank,
no surprise there.
They've really only got
each other at this point.
And also, it was kind of
painfully obvious
that Kim Powers is
kind of on her own.
But there are people
taking care of her there.
- Thanks, Big Tom.
- I remember you sitting there,
and the last thing you said,
"Oh, what I'd give for
ice cream," and I went...
- It was interesting to
see who's a more clever and
shrewd wheeler and dealer.
Tom probably walked away the
biggest winner as far as food.
- Pancake, did you
like the pancake?
- Yeah, really.
I made out like
a bandit.
- You got
your ham, Big Tom.
- Tom, he is not the most
politically correct human being,
so when he said that he was
sharing the ham with
a Jew boy, knowing that
he wasn't going to eat it,
I was like,
"Oh, my God."
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, that was...
- I'm a Caucasian,
call me anything.
What am I?
C- A bigot..
- What is a bigot?
- I mean, at this point,
I don't really take offense.
I know he's joking.
You know, he doesn't
really mean it.
- Man, you can
play some checkers.
He thinks a lot
before he moves.
- Me and Tom, we have kind of
like almost like a brotherly
relationship right now.
He makes fun of me 'cause I'm
Jewish and I make fun of him
'cause he's fat and he's
got a boil on his neck
and there's just, like,
competition, you know,
he's going to
beat me at checkers.
Oh... man.
- Don't do that.
- He's a checker shark.
- I go back and forth on
whether or not I think Tom is
for real or some of it's put on,
because I think he's smarter
than he lets on.
- Stupid me.
- Tommy, he plays a good old
boy, but I don't think he's as
backwoods-ish as he would like
to make you think.
- Checkmate.
- We're just
totally done already?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God,
that's pathetic.
- He's very good.
- You know, his whole, you
know, "I'm a hayseed from
Virginia, I'm not
that smart."
I knew quickly that he was a lot
brighter than he let on.
And actually, I mean that
endeared me to him and intrigued
me all the more.
- What do you two
think you're doing?
- You're both going
forward.
- You're back to back.
- Well, the door's
this way.
- That's funny.
- Are you
all right now?
- Yeah.
- Are they zebra?
- Yeah,
those are zebra.
- That's a nice, little herd,
ain't it?
- Yeah, a big herd.
- Thundering herd.
- Hey, mama cat,
bring it on up here.
- Okay.
- We have been kind of in
a routine, so today, to keep
things fresh, we went to our
watering hole, put our stuff
down and Big Tom
gave everyone a little shower.
- Oh, man.
- Tommy, I'll take a shower.
- Okay, brother.
- We have been here a while,
and we were getting pretty
comfortable with each other,
and I can change
without being too
worried if anyone sees me.
You know, I can fart, you know,
and not really care.
- All right,
girls, back off.
- You can douse me.
When you spend 30 days with
people in very close proximity,
you're not ashamed or bashful of
just about anything anymore.
I mean, we've lived together
closer than most families live
together and bathing or
whatever, it just seems like
it's something that you kind of
have to do it, and you really
don't care who
sees you anymore.
- Tom's loving
every minute of it.
- Woo-hoo, does that
feel good!
- Tom gets away with murder.
Like today, you know, he was
having a good time bathing the
ladies, having them kind of pull
their bathing suits back.
- Don't think Tom doesn't
know what he's doing.
- Tom's not washing you...
at all.
- I mean,
Tommy's harmless.
It's not, like, he's going to,
like, jump our bones there
or anything.
He's really harmless and if he
gets a peek, you know,
more power to him.
It doesn't do
any good for anybody
to take offense at
anybody.
It only costs you friendship,
and this whole exercise out here
I think is about getting along
with people and just going
with the flow.
- One for the road!
- Encore!
- We have been here a while and
we're getting pretty comfortable
with each other, and it's like
your family now.
And it makes everything a little
more difficult because tomorrow,
I'm going to have to vote
one of these people off.
- (Probst) Hey, guys, welcome to
this abandoned boma.
You'll be playing
today's challenge here.
As always, first
things first.
I'll take this back.
Immunity is back
up for grabs.
Okay.
Today's challenge is going to
test how well you remember
the African story
I'm about to tell you.
But first, here's what
you'll have to do.
We've set up seven gated
stations, and only one person at
a time can be there,
so make sure you
close the gate behind you.
Each station has a question and
two ostrich eggs.
Break open the egg
for the correct answer.
You'll find a piece of
colored leather.
Wrap that around
the same color on your staff.
If you answer incorrectly,
you'll find nothing, you'll have
to try again later.
The eggs will be replaced after
each person leaves the station.
First person back in the circle
with five of the seven questions
answered correctly and five
pieces of leather on their staff
wins immunity.
Okay, story time.
Today, I'm going to tell you
about the Samburu warrior.
When a baby boy is born,
his destiny is already planned.
To celebrate the birth,
a goat is sacrificed.
The women of the tribe eat
the meat of the goat because
the women are the caretakers
of the tribe.
For the first four days after
the birth, the mother drinks
only the blood
of the goat.
Around the age
of nine or ten,
the boy has his first
rite of passage.
This is the removal of his two
bottom middle teeth because if
he were to get sick and they
needed to get food or water into
his body, they use the gap from
the two missing teeth as a way
to do that.
It's also around this time that
he begins the practice of
piercing his ears.
This is the first cosmetic
enhancement.
His next rite of passage is a
circumcision, and that begins
with a journey
to find gum from a special tree.
It could take him as long 45
days, during which he can only
subsist on
the generosity of others--
the food that he gets
along the way.
Once he's
completed his mission,
a date for the circumcision
is set.
Dates are scheduled
based on the new moon.
The tribe will wait for any
even-numbered day of moonlight.
Eighth day, considered
the best day.
In preparation for a
circumcision, shaves his head.
But the most important aspect
to a circumcision
is a warrior's reaction.
If, during the circumcision,
he flinches in any way,
he and his
family are forever shamed.
After eight years of
warriorship,
he's eligible
for marriage.
Tribal custom demands that he
continue to have kids until he
has a boy, even if that means
taking another wife and another.
The last step: Death.
Once a warrior is close to
death, he is taken into the bush
with another warrior
and left to die.
Once he dies, fellow warriors
shave their heads out of
respect, and his body is
left for the hyenas to eat.
From birth to death,
a hard life.
Now we're going to see
what you've learned.
Grab your staffs
and let's get it on.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Make sure
you close your gates.
- Food provided by others.
- "What happens
after a warrior dies?"
- Oh, hell.
Well, I can't cry over spilt
milk.
I missed it.
- (Probst) Frank and Lex,
each with one.
- "Reaction of
the warrior."
- "What must be done
when a child is born?"
- (Probst) Lex, Frank and
Kim Johnson all have one.
- "Eighth day of moonlight."
- "The reaction
of the warrior."
- (Probst) Teresa and Kim Powers
now also have one.
- "First act of tribal
beautification is: removal of
"the two bottom teeth,
piercing of the ear.
Piercing of the ear."
- (Probst) Lex and Frank
in the lead with two each.
- Oh, hell.
That ain't right.
- "Body left in the bush
for hyenas to eat."
Or maybe not!
- "Shave his head."
- (Probst) Lex and Frank
lead with four.
Everybody else at three.
- (Probst) You got it, Lex?
- One, two, three, four.
I dropped one.
- (Probst) Gotta find it, Lex.
Gotta find it.
Lex says he has five,
but he can't find his fifth.
Get it on there, baby.
Lex trying to get his
in the right spot.
We're still alive.
- God.
I've got to be careful.
- Lex wins
immunity again.
Lex, again, you're not
going down.
Con- Thanks.ons.
- (Probst) You're safe
from the vote.
Somebody else
is going home.
I'll see you
at Tribal Council.
- To be here is just awesome.
This morning's sunrise is just,
is just, so beautiful.
You know, I don't think the
majority of people in our
everyday, busy lives take a
moment to just watch something
as beautiful as that, and to
suddenly realize just how small
we are in the world, and how
time can just pass by in a
moment and we
would be gone.
You know, it puts your life
back in perspective.
- Nice sunrise.
- Oh, my God.
- Look at that.
- My love for being here grows
every day.
Just loving the outdoors, you
know, and the animals and
wildlife and people in a way, as
well, you know, I love to mingle
with people.
Good morning, Ethan.
- Good morning.
- H- Good.you?
- Breakfast.
- Are we having soup?
- Uh-huh.
- I love your soup.
-- I love the soup.
- Good.
Good, good, good.
- As always, very tasty.
I mean, really.
- It's just a beautiful
morning, so I was just adding to
the wonderful atmosphere and
just socializing and, you know,
let them see there's a soft,
sensual side of me.
My argument always with the
gun, you know, activist, is that
they think that guns
kill people.
There's, like... there's
everything else you could kill
someone with, you know, a piece
of fishing line I can kill
somebody with.
- Hit them over the head
with a brick.
- You know, automobiles kill
people every day, drug overdose,
malpractice,
just everything.
- All right, enough.
- Frank seems really
rambunctious this morning
and he's talking a lot.
And he's a very opinionated
person, which is fine, but,
like, when you have immunity at
stake, you kind of just need to
keep your mouth shut.
- I can't help it.
These little, liberal special
interest groups that the media
give open market to instead of
the average working-class
Americans that
founded this country.
- All right! All right!
- Well, what can I say
about Frank?
Once again, Frank is Frank.
- You know, Ray might
invite me to their banquet,
their convention
down there.
- Perfect.
- He brings up
this gun stuff.
And Lex is going
like this, you know.
Ethan's sitting over there, not
saying a word, but I can tell
it's getting to him, too.
And I'm thinking to myself,
Frank, cut it, stop.
Why is it on the days that you
need to be most careful of how
you act and what you say, Frank,
like, goes off on the A.R. or
whatever stuff?
- Yeah.
Well, that's just the way...
he ain't going to change.
- Today is
Tribal Council day.
Today is the day
that you don't
want to really
ruffle any feathers.
But, you know, I started out
from the very beginning with an
alliance with
Frank, and shoot,
I've been here for
this many days.
I'm sure not
going to give up now.
- This is all going exactly
as we wanted it to.
Things couldn't
be any better.
- The guys have dominated
the game.
They're saying who goes next.
If nothing else, I'd like to see
the women get in there.
- Right.
- Teresa doesn't
want to give up,
and I don't want
to give up either.
So, Teresa is, like, trying to
scramble and figure out
it there's
anything that we can do.
- Ethan's going to take
the whole thing.
He's great.
What can you say
negative about Ethan?
Nothing.
- It's a shot in the dark, but
if I can persuade Kim to vote
off Ethan, that would break up
that alliance.
- If Ethan's not here...
- That would leave Kim,
you, me and Frank.
- You, me and Frank.
- And then you're going to
stick by Frank.
- No.
If you do this tonight, then
I'll pledge my loyalty to you.
It could hurt me going to Kim,
but Ethan's bonded with those
guys, and they're going to be
strong enough every time they
vote to weed off
one more of us.
So it's kind of a risk, but at
this point, I feel like this is
the only chance I've got.
- I was really
shocked and pissed
that they would even,
you know....
- Well, they're cornered.
They have
no options.
- Teresa approached me with the
idea that Tommy, Lex and Ethan
really don't have any kind of
allegiance toward me,
but I just can't
turn on Ethan at this point.
So I'm going to have to tell
Teresa that, and I'm not sure
what the reaction is
going to be to that.
I just think, so really, that I
think I might still be shooting
myself in the foot, even if I
could bring myself to it do it.
- Okay, I understand.
I just appreciate you're telling
us so we can do different stuff.
- I had an opportunity,
obviously, to do something to
save them, and I didn't
do that.
And now I'm afraid
it's going to hurt me.
- This plan's not coming
together.
- I know it's not.
- So, it'll be an interesting
Tribal Council.
- (Probst) We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
30 days.
Congratulations.
You made it a long ways.
Basically a month
out here on your own.
Well, obviously, from this point
forward, the power shifts from
the tribe members left
to the jury that is growing.
Your dilemma is obvious: How can
you vote somebody out of this
game, take that million dollars
out of their hand and then ask
them to put it in your hands
by voting you most deserving?
Teresa, what goes through your
head now as you show up tonight
and here's Brandon
and Kelly?
People you had
a hand in voting out,
you're going to need
them later.
- For me, I guess it takes just
the way I play the game,
trying to be as
honest with everybody,
you know, that I could be,
so at this point,
it's just playing as
fair as I can and hope that
they'll respect, you know, my
decisions and how I played.
- (Probst) Ethan, one of you
seven is going tonight.
Next Tribal Council, they'll be
sitting over there.
How can you vote them out
and ask them to vote
for you at the end?
- Well, you've just got to hope
that what you did before the
vote and how you treated people
before the vote will, you know,
put you in a good light.
It is just a game,
and if you get voted out,
it's just a
strategy.
You've got to look out
for yourself in the end.
- (Probst) Lex, how close is
this game to turning ugly?
- I think the game has already
gone through some ugly times.
I think it's taken
a turn for the better.
It's probably going to
get ugly again.
But everyone here, whether
they're, you know, sitting up
here or on the jury, realizes,
though, that they came to play
a game and to win.
And you can do that with
integrity, but to come in here
thinking that it's never going
to be, you know,
just a bones-to-bones
competition is to be naive.
- (Probst) Frank, do you feel
like it's still the old Samburu
and the old Boran when it comes
down to voting?
- Not really because the game
is changing, you know.
I think those old
tribal names are gone.
Our tribe had a new name,
everyone belonged to it.
I think it's a strategy within
the new tribe.
- (Probst) Kim, do you feel that
you might be safer because maybe
people don't see you as such a
physical threat,
or are you worried that
maybe you're too likable
and, therefore, you've
got to go?
- I'm always worried.
I think I would be worried if
I were strong and I'm worried
because I'm not so strong.
It doesn't matter
how nice I am
or how weak I am or
how strong I am.
If I'm the logical
person to go, I'm going.
- All right, it's time
to vote.
Lex is the only
one you can't vote for.
Everybody else
is fair game.
Kim, you're up first.
- I've enjoyed you as a person,
but we have to vote somebody off
and you're my
next logical choice.
I'll miss you, though.
- It's been good for me to be
around someone so different from
myself and learn from you.
I'm glad that we actually got to
spend some time together.
- This is not
a vote of betrayal.
This is a vote
of strategy.
Frank, thank you so much
for the friendship.
- I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Frank.
Kim Johnson.
Frank.
Three votes Frank,
one vote Kim.
Frank.
That's enough, Frank.
You need to bring me
your torch.
Frank, the tribe
has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
You guys can head
back to camp.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
- (Probst) Next time
on Survivor:
Teresa pushes the
all-girl alliance.
- I really don't want to see
the guys come down to the end.
- Bye, babies.
- (Probst) The members of Moto
Maji get videos from home.
And the winner
of the reward challenge
takes the trip of a
lifetime.
- To my lovely wife, Polly,
and my daughters, Jocelyn Rose
and Sage Hunter.
Thank you for your unselfish
sacrifices you made so I could
go on this adventure.
I give you my word of honor that
down the road, I will make
all your dreams come true.
As your husband, as your father
and as your friend, I love you
and I miss you,
thank you.