- (Jeff Probst)
Previously on Survivor...
All bets were off when the game
took a drastic twist.
Silas, Teresa, Frank, you
guys are now members of Boran.
Kelly, Lex, Tom, you guys are
now members of Samburu.
- No, what?
- (Probst)
At Samburu, Lindsey,
Brandon and Kim were shocked to
meet their new tribe mates.
- I'm just, like...
- (Probst)
At Boran, Ethan, Kim
and Clarence had the same
surprise.
- Hey, you got
a nice holster.
- I'm definitely on the other
side right now.
I was on the good side,
now I'm on the bad side.
- Frank and I looked at each
other and thought, "You know..."
- We're alive again.
- (Probst) Boran won three
egg-laying chickens
and a rooster
at the reward challenge.
Boran wins!
- Boran!
- (Probst) But Samburu won
the immunity challenge...
(cheering)
...sending Boran
to Tribal Council,
where Silas was voted
out of the tribe.
Well, there's been
a lot of assumptions made by you
guys so far in this game.
One of them is that in three
days there will be a merge.
11 are left.
Tonight,
one more will go.
♪♪
(clucking)
- You know, during our
questioning, Jeff's, like,
"Ethan, with this
merger coming up,
are you vulnerable getting
voted off?"
So the merger is coming up.
- My gut feeling would be, if
the merger was changed from the
norm, that it would be sooner
rather than later.
- Well,
I think either way,
beginning tomorrow morning we're
just going to have to be ready
for whatever comes.
- Right.
- The whole thing with the
merge is driving me insane.
At the end of Tribal Council the
other night, Jeff said,
"You guys assume
the merge is in three days."
So, you know, he throws
the question out there.
He throws
the thought out there.
Put it in our head that, like,
oh, my God, maybe the merge
isn't in three days.
We rationed our food so we're
ending all our food at
the merger,
which is in three days.
If we eat all our food and
there's no merger after three
days, we have no food.
- We have three chickens.
- We need to decide,
do we stay
with our normal
food intake, do we ration?
I mean, how do you guys
want to proceed?
- We prepa- Yeah.the worst.
- I mean, what happens
if it's in ten days?
We're screwed.
(crickets chirping)
- I got another hour
before daylight.
- Mm-hmm.
- (whispers) We got, like,
five-hour watch.
I think we came out
about 1:00 in the morning.
Tom and I took in a long night
shift last night.
Everyone else took about an hour
and a half, two hours, and we
got, like... we got stuck with
about five hours.
We've been staying up all night
for over two weeks.
These guys have no concept
of what a three-hour shift is.
They just throw a log on
the fire and go to bed.
- That sucks.
- I know, it's terrible,
but she just does
not want to do it at all.
- I think Lindsey's heart is in
the right place.
- Oh, yeah,
she's a sweet girl.
- She's just a big...
- It was painfully obvious the
moment we stepped foot in camp
here that, you know, we had
three people here that...
they were here for
a little resort vacation.
They weren't here
to do anything
but nap and eat
and make a couple meals.
- How was your guys'
last shift?
Was it
too long, too short?
- It was at least
five hours.
- Was it, really?
Everyone is
stressed out right now.
This whole switcheroo
thing has made
everyone's mind
kind of go crazy.
Everyone is thinking, "Oh, we're
two new tribes now.
Let's not think
of our old tribes."
But it's inevitable,
you're going to think of
your old tribe.
- I want to know who the hell
got the boot.
- Frank is a target.
- I think everyone
will vote for him.
- I hope so.
- People just want to see
what's shaking up at Boran,
because what goes on over there
could totally affect
what happens over here.
- What do you think?
- I'm concerned that Kim may
have gotten canned.
- We know if we get beat in a
challenge, we've got our vote,
and we know it's going to be
three-three.
They're going to pick out
somebody on us, and we're going
to pick out somebody
on them.
But the key to the vote
is what's happened before.
- If we have to go to
Tribal Council,
it's all
about past votes.
If we have a tie, it comes down
to who has more votes, then I
already have four votes
against me, so I'd be gone.
- Three more nights y'all have
got with us.
- God, I'm glad
we got you guys.
- Yeah, we lucked out,
we did really, really well.
- I'm really trying to save my
own butt, you know?
I don't want them to have any
clue about my situation.
I mean, I set a goal for myself,
and I am the kind of person that
when I set a goal,
I'm going to achieve it.
- I can't stop
thinking about food.
I dream about food.
I think about food when I'm
eating food.
I think about food 24/7.
Any - No.yet?
- Ah, you know what that
means-- chopping-block day.
- Since we got those
chickens,
we'll have to
keep an eye on you.
Every time you walk
by the cage,
we'll have to
keep an eye on you.
- I will not deny that I'm
having homicidal feelings about
those damn chickens.
- What do
you guys think?
What do you and Kim think about
the chicken situation?
- I don't know.
I mean, you just
want to eat them?
- I'- Yeah, me, too.gs.
- For some reason I don't know
that that's going to happen.
- Yeah.
Some people want to eat
the chickens right away,
like Clarence,
and some people want to wait
to see if they'll lay
some eggs.
It's just, the problem is, if we
go to the merger and we're not
allowed to take the chickens,
then it's a waste.
- Chicken nuggets.
- Clarence, are they acting
like they're thinking about
laying eggs?
- Hell, no.
I'm breaking straw for your
little asses.
Lay some eggs.
- The chickens are presently
still up for debate, but we're
going to wait till today's
reward challenge to see
what's available
today and then probably
make a decision
tonight.
- Whatever it is,
I hope there's no animals.
No goats, chickens.
The only animal I want is
something that's going to be on
a plate, that I could eat.
That's all I want,
just food.
- Good old food.
- Yep, there is mail.
You ready?
- Yeah.
- "Stick with your tribe.
"Make your
way to the bottom.
"Just give us your answers,
that is, if you got 'em.
"You must work as
a team, confer with your bunch.
Make a wrong move and watch
the others eat lunch."
- Oh, that's good.
- The reward they said is
"lunch," so the food-- maybe,
we'll go someplace,
and have a
nice sit-down
lunch-slash-dinner.
- "Make your way to
the bottom."
That's the clue in there.
- Maybe it's, like, a giant
board game or something.
- How comfortable are you guys
with all the stuff in the book?
Pretty good with
all that?
Today's tree mail indicates
that it's probably something
sort of cerebral.
We've been studying
all the things we learned in our
survival manual-- the desert out
here, and the plants and
the animals-- hoping that
we can win us a free lunch.
- Silas is gone,
Silas is gone.
Oh, my God.
- (Probst)
Hey, guys.
Samburu, getting
your first look
at the latest member of Boran
to be voted out.
Silas is gone.
Reactions? Surprised?
-- No.h.
- No... no.
- All right, today for
your reward challenge, I'm going
to ask you a series of questions
about Africa, and you'll answer
each question as a tribe.
Each time you get one right,
you move one step down on
the bleacher, one step
closer to the finish.
First tribe to reach the finish
gets the reward.
Want to know what
you're playing for?
- Yes, sir.
- Oh...
- Oh, my God.
(excited shouts)
- (braying)
- It's cold, too.
- Oh...
- (Probst) Just to
whet your whistle,
I'm going to give you
guys a little taste.
Tell me that's not going to
taste good, huh, Clarence?
(chuckling)
- Ah, it's so good.
- Yeah!
- (Probst) Okay,
the Mountain Dew
is just a little bit
of a tease.
Here's the rest of what you're
playing for.
Got a nice little
buffet set out for you here.
- - Wow.d.
- Oh, my God.
- (Probst) Fresh pasta
with vegetables.
We got a huge
tray of sandwiches.
And a big old plate of
cookies...
- Oh-ho-ho!
- (Probst)
...for dessert.
Not to mention, all the Mountain
Dew you can drink.
- O- Oh...!d!
- (Probst) How good is that
going to taste for somebody?
All right, Samburu, 'cause you
have one extra person,
you've chosen
Tom to sit out.
Guys, head to the top
of the bleachers.
Wait for my start.
Here we go.
First question.
True or false?
"The closest ocean
to Kenya is the Atlantic."
Okay, show me
your answer.
Boran says "false."
Samburu says "false."
You're both right.
Indian Ocean,
closest ocean.
Move down a level.
True or false?
"To save the elephant population
in Kenya, military rangers are
instructed to
shoot to kill ivory poachers."
True or false?
(inaudible whispering)
Let's reveal.
"True," says Samburu.
Boran says "true."
You're both right.
Next question.
"On safari, the animals known as
the 'Big Five' are the elephant,
rhino, lion, buffalo,
and what other animal?"
A) Leopard, B) Tiger,
C) Giraffe, or D) Hippo.
(inaudible whispering)
- (whispers)
I know this, I know this.
- (Probst) Reveal.
A, says Samburu,
"leopard."
D, says Boran. "Hippo."
Correct answer,
A) leopard.
Samburu moves
one step closer.
- I'm sorry, guys.
- (Probst) Next question.
"Diurnal is a term
to describe what?"
A) Animals that must eat plants
as well as meat to stay healthy,
B) Animals that
hunt in groups,
C) animals that are more
prevalent by day,
or D) Animals that do not eat
humans but pose a threat through
the diseases
they may carry.
Diurnal.
(inaudible whispering)
Let's reveal.
Samburu says
C) More prevalent by day.
Boran says C.
You're both right.
You guys need to stand.
Samburu is now
at their last step.
One more correct answer,
you guys are having
a nice, big old fat lunch.
Here we go.
True or false?
"Kenya's Lake Victoria is the
world's largest saltwater lake."
(inaudible whispering)
All right, Samburu.
Reveal.
Samburu says "false."
Boran
says "false."
It is actually not the largest,
and it is freshwater.
Bon appétit, Samburu.
(cheering, whooping)
- Yeah!
- Oh, my God!
- (Probst) Samburu,
your food's waiting.
- I'm, like, all nervous.
Like it's a first date.
I'm, like, is the food
going to reject me?
- Oh, God.
- Oh, my God, oh, my God,
chocolate!
- Mayonnaise. Mustard.
- Oh, my Gosh.
Oh, look at
this sandwich.
- Oh, my God,
an ice cube.
- Tell me what you want.
- Shortbread.
- This is the best cheese
sandwich I've ever had.
- I swear to God, it's the best
thing I've ever tasted.
- Oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God.
- It's just like a picnic.
- Hey, we're breaking bread
together... great.
- Proper, we're
breaking bread proper.
- Proper.
- - Bon appétit.s.
- Have a nice weekend.
- Oh, my God.
- It has been
a real pleasure.
- Our new team.
(cheering, whooping)
- Remember the Dew!
(man belches)
- Oh, that was a good one.
- Oh, my God.
- You'll be okay,
just go slow.
- I am sweating.
My heart is racing.
My stomach hurts like I have
never felt before in my life.
- The food reward was amazing,
I mean, we just pigged out.
And our stomachs, you know,
they've shrunk,
so it's-- it's
hard to stuff food in there and
let them expand, but we sure
found a way.
- Just take it real slow
and easy, then.
- Oh, my God.
- Better to hold
this down if you can.
- Kim gorged on stuff her body
wasn't used to, and her tiny
little, you know,
five foot one figure
isn't going to hold all
that very well.
So she was
pretty close to vomiting.
- (groans)
- Just stick your finger
down your throat.
- No, no, no,
just let her take her time.
Let her take her time.
- Look at her belly!
(laughter)
- It is pooching out.
- Oh, do- It's okay. laugh.
- You're going to be a vomit
launch extravaganza.
- Kim, if you barf,
just barf a little bit of it out
and then keep the rest.
- Oh, my God.
- Luckily, we were all
able to hold it down.
We were all
very proud of ourselves.
And having all this energy
stored up should definitely give
us an edge, I hope.
- Oh, I feel good.
- That felt really good.
- (groans)
- The weather today has been
awesome.
We got a full meal,
and we got rid of Silas.
- Oh, he's probably
just fuming!
When I saw that
Silas was gone, my heart sank.
I was definitely shocked.
- I never would have guessed he
had votes against him, and you
would think it would come down
three and three.
- You know why
Silas has votes against him?
'cause Frank tried to get Silas
in an alliance
and - Really.d no.
- So Frank went ballistic.
- That is bizarre.
- Yeah. It was awful.
It was a total showdown.
When we had the upper hand, we
treated Frank and Teresa poorly.
Especially me, I gloated, and
I was excited and I felt like
I was the queen of the land,
which was a bad move on my part.
And I think they were definitely
out for some kind of revenge.
- Frank must have totally sold
out Silas, 'cause there's no way
they would have known
to vote for him.
- Oh, yeah, that's exac--
that's what I mean.
- What a little pig.
- I told Lindsey that probably
was a big part of them switching
to Silas, you know, because
y'all got in their face, and you
have to really think about it,
if they're backed into a corner.
Looks to me like we're the ones
kind of over the pit now.
- I think for
the rest of my life,
I want to be a food
critic.
I'm going to be called
the "man's man's food critic."
You know what I'm saying?
The "meat-and-potatoes
food critic."
When people see me coming,
they better be on their game.
Your French fries better be
extra greasy.
Your pancakes
better be extra fluffy.
- Let the rest of them fools
critique all those fancy French
sushi places.
- Clarence, if anyone,
is probably having the most
difficult time controlling
wanting to get his fingers on
some fried chicken, more or
less, you know.
Which I don't blame him, but
it's no way to play the game and
for down the road, for a
valuable resource, so...
Hey, we'll still all get an
egg, maybe.
We'll get an egg
or two, hopefully.
- The members of my tribe,
they're of the opinion that
given the right environment, our
chickens are going to lay eggs,
which is completely...
a joke to me.
(chickens clucking)
- Believe it or not, I think
we're all unsure what the hens
need to do to lay
the eggs.
Frank wants to
put a net out there
so they can run around
and play.
(quiet laugh)
- Oh, giving
you something nice.
I think that's better for them,
don't you?
- One of you say
your good-byes.
Don't get mad.
Don't get mad, man.
- Oh, she's telling you.
- Don't get mad.
Tribal Council
for you tonight.
- As much as we're
joking about it,
I am serious about killing
one of those chickens.
(knife scraping)
You know, I've talked to each
one of the chickens personally,
and I've informed them that,
you know, they're on notice.
- Last night you told them you
loved them and...
- I do, man. I also told them,
you know, you got 24 hours to
lay an egg,
and now technically,
it'll be 48 hours, so that's
on them.
- What if they lay an egg by
tomorrow morning?
- Then we spare them.
How's that?
- I swear.
- You hear that,
you guys?
Clarence says if
we find an egg in the morning,
the chicken lives.
- All they have to do
is lay an egg, one egg.
- I mean, we don't know what's
happened over there.
I mean, we have no idea,
like, they have no idea that all
of us are over here totally
getting along.
- Yeah, that's true.
- I'm kind of loving it.
I kind of think it's cool.
- I've had some moments with
Kelly that I feel like we've
sort of bonded and we've had a
good time, and she has expressed
that she's fearful of her
demise, so...
She seems pretty genuine.
- (whispers)
I think Kelly really likes her.
- I think they really like
all three of us.
But that has
nothing to do with it.
We cannot vote for Lindsey.
If she gets voted against, I'm
gone in the next six days.
And that's
the same with you.
And that's not
good enough.
- If we have to go to a Tribal
Council, we're assuming that it
will go to a tiebreaker and
they'll ask us questions from
this handbook.
- Which is what
they did the last time.
- Which is what they did
the last time.
- But, see, you're not, I mean,
you don't see the big picture.
They are not... they are not
going to vote for you.
They like you more than me,
'cause I have haven't been
trying to be
all that extra nice to them.
I just haven't.
I mean, I don't care.
(rooster crowing)
(chickens clucking)
- Good morning,
boys and girls.
Did you guys
leave us any eggs?
(chickens clucking)
I went into the cage this
morning, and I didn't see
anything in the beginning at
all, and I thought, "Oh, damn,
these chickens didn't lay
any eggs again."
(quietly)
Yay. Look at this.
Look at this,
you guys. Yay.
Yes, yes.
Yes, we have eggs.
- Oh, don't tell...
She's got
something in her hand.
- (whistling a tune)
- I'll be damned.
Look at that, see?
You've got an egg,
right?
Oh, yeah!
Great.
- Isn't that cool?
Let's just put it right there.
- Just let it sit there.
- So we're just going to keep
it right on the tray there until
Clarence wakes up
and sees the egg.
(imitates Clarence)
Oh, damn!
Damn, those chickens.
We finally
have an egg.
- I loved it this morning when
Kim brought over that egg.
'cause last night Clarence was,
like, "Well, one of them have an
egg, we don't have to
eat the chicken."
- An egg!
- Shh.
- (whispers) Wow!
- Shh. He's coming.
- What's up?
- What's up,
Clarence?
- Aw, hell, no!
Come on!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
(whooping, cheering)
- No chicken for you!
- I hate you
and you and you
and you, and you did it just to
spite me, so whatever.
And you laid... and they laid
the smallest egg possible, too.
(laughter)
If you scramble that egg,
it might disappear.
(laughter)
Oh, I hate those
chickens.
- Truth is,
I don't think any
of us mind killing a chicken
for dinner.
- We tormented him a little
bit, but we decided we were
going to kill a chicken and eat
it for dinner anyway.
- You can come to my house
and carve a Thanksgiving
turkey anytime.
- Mmm.
- Oh, my God.
The chicken tastes great.
Everyone had a hand in preparing
it, and, I mean, I was just,
wow, it was just... mwah!
- Oh.
(chuckling)
- Oh, God.
- Oka- Wow.l...
- How good is that?
- Mmm.
- Since our arrival, Teresa and
I, we've been smiling.
It's been a very
comfortable transition.
Thank you, everyone.
You know,
I wish we would have
been here from day one with
these people.
- Y'all, that was
very delicious.
♪♪
- (whispering)
That makes sense.
I can't believe I never thought
of that, why Kim was doing it.
- No, I didn't know she was
doing this.
- She did it at the...
- All I saw her do
is this.
- She did
that yesterday, too.
- I'm such an idiot.
All this time, Kim, at the
challenges, she was doing this.
I'm, like, what does
this mean, lose?
Do you want me
to throw the challenge?
What's the L? The L?
Then I'm sitting there, and I'm,
like, "Oh, Lindsey."
Obviously, she thinks
Lindsey has votes against her.
And also I think she was trying
to tell me Brandon.
Because if she was doing
something like this, I don't
know, I think it's "B"
in sign language.
She knows sign language.
I don't know it.
- They were totally
communicating,
and I was like...
"What's going on?"
And she kept going...
- They were trying to
tell them something.
I don't know if it was, you
know, vote for Lindsey,
she has votes, or...
I don't know.
- I... I think
we need to go
with the safest bet,
as we've said all along.
- I mean, we're playing
hard ball now.
- Yeah, that's true.
- We're pretty sure that
Brandon already has votes
against him.
We suspected that
from the start.
Knowing that Frank had been
in the same tribe with him,
we figured if there was anybody
that Frank was just going to
throw a vote at just on
principal alone, it would have
been Brandon.
- I don't know what they're
thinking, but I don't have any
votes, so I still think I have
a really good chance.
But if they vote for Lindsey,
then it's done, she's gone.
Out of the three of us, they're
gonna be most likely to think
that I have a vote from Frank,
you know what I mean?
- That's why they think they're
sitting pretty, it's because
they assume
that you have a vote.
- They just assume that I have
a vote from Frank.
- Should we just vote
for Tom and stick to it?
- We stick with it.
That's it, period.
- (loud snoring)
- We're totally confident that
if it's a three-and-three tie
against Brandon and Tom, that
Brandon can win the questions.
- (groaning)
- I mean, Kelly, she's like
a walking thesaurus, and Lex
probably is too much
of a chance, too.
So we think we're going to vote
for Tom, knowing that Brandon
could probably
beat him in trivia.
- I'm going to do it,
there's just no way around it.
There's no way I can lose to
him, unless it's...
I can't imagine what question
they would ask that he would
know and I wouldn't.
I mean, I told the girls this
is what we would do.
I'll have to just
take a bullet for her.
Let's have a group hug.
Come here.
- It looks like they're still
a little divided, so it probably
will be a three-three vote on
their side.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- And hopefully they got
the clue that Lindsey has four
votes, and they'll vote her.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yes!
- (both) "To bring home
the bounty, the key is to aim.
"If you can't hit the mark,
there's no one to blame.
"It may seem
so easy, but lest ye confuse,
the last tribe to do it
will pick one to lose."
- So everyone's
got to do it.
- Yep.
- So Frank can teach us all
how to do it, which is good.
- Oh, that's right,
he's a hunter.
- You know, immediately they
read the mail, and it was going
to take a team effort
by all of us.
So being what I consider
proficient somewhat in archery,
I was immediately thrust right
into the limelight.
Okay, T, here's
the line, right here.
Point your left foot
right at the target.
Got it?
Index finger on top,
let it seep.
Lean a little forward, draw
back, and hold that form until
the arrow hits the ground.
Okay.
That's a start.
- Frank, I'm starting
to figure
out about Frank
is he's a teacher.
He loves instruction.
You know, I think that probably
comes from a little bit, mostly
from the military,
in terms of giving orders.
- Now, wait a minute, wait a
minute, wait a minute.
Are you plan- No.on shooting?
- Oh, okay, because you are
loaded right now.
It's like having
a gun right now in your hand.
- Frank, definitely, I mean,
this is Frank's thing.
He's very, you know, vocal and
giving us all the help he can.
- Okay.
It's a timing issue.
- Without him, you know,
I wouldn't know all the little
stuff that could bring us
the win later on.
- Very good,
straight arrow.
See how nice and straight
that went?
- (whoops)
Beautiful!
- That's very nice,
nicely done.
- This immunity challenge is
important, because right now,
although on paper the old Boran
tribe has a one-person edge,
you still don't
know what's going on.
- Yes.
- (Probst)
First things first.
Lindsey, got to take back
immunity idol.
Immunity is
back up for grabs.
As you can see, we have some
fires, nice and smoky, burning.
Those will come into play for
today's immunity challenge.
We're going to test your
proficiency with
a bow and arrow.
Each tribe has five targets,
ranging from 30 to 70 feet.
You'll square off against each
other, one member from each
tribe taking one shot,
then the next pair will go.
First tribe using lighted arrows
to light up all five targets
wins immunity,
avoids the vote.
Pick your first shooter
and wait for my go.
Samburu, because you have one
extra member, you've chosen
Kelly to sit out.
First shooters,
take your spot.
- All right, Kim!
- Let's go!
- (whooping)
- (Probst)
Grab an arrow, guys.
Ready.
Take your aim.
And fire.
- Close.
- Good job, good job.
- Good shot.
- Nice try.
- (Probst)
Next two.
- All right, Lindsey!
- (Probst)
Take your aim.
And fire.
- All right!
(cheering, whooping)
- (Probst)
Samburu up one-oh.
Ethan and Brandon,
you're up.
Ready.
Take your aim.
And fire.
- Aw.
- Close.
- (yells)
Sorry.
- (Probst)
Lex and Clarence.
Take your aim.
Fire.
(cheering)
That's a hit!
- Great!
- (Probst) Samburu two,
Boran one.
- All right, Big T!
- (Probst)
Fire at will.
Two good shots,
two misses.
Samburu two,
Boran one.
Round two.
- Come on,
you can do this.
- (Probst) Take your aim.
And fire.
No.
That's a hit.
Boran connects, two-two.
- Yeah!
- Nice, Ethan.
- All right, Lex.
(cheering)
- (Probst) Samburu hits.
Samburu up three-two.
And fire.
- Oh, my...
- (Probst)
That's a hit.
Three-three.
Tied up.
(cheering)
- Good job!
- All right, Tom!
- (Probst) Here's where we're
at-- Samburu leads four-three.
Almost, Frank.
Next round, guys.
Take your aim.
Fire.
- Oh!
- Okay, you were close.
- All right, Lindsey, you got
it, you got it.
You almost hit
this one last time.
- (Probst) Next two.
- You got it, Lindsey.
- All right,
Lindsey.
- Take your aim.
And fire.
- Yeah!
(whooping)
- Here's where we're at--
tied up, Samburu four,
Boran four.
Lindsey, you could win
immunity right here.
- Oh!
- (Probst) Next target hit
wins immunity.
All right, guys.
Fire at will.
- (speaks inaudibly)
- Yeah!
(cheering)
- (Probst)
Immunity for Boran!
- Yes! Yes!
- (Probst) Samburu, you know
what this means, right?
See you at Tribal Council.
♪♪
- We gave it
our best shot.
So we find ourselves faced with
Tribal Council today, which puts
us all in a potentially
vulnerable position.
Because now, you know,
we find ourselves having to...
to vote
someone out.
- You and I have not talked at
all about this thing tonight.
- Right, and you're trying to
figure out if I have a vote?
- No, I'm not... I'm not
here to ask you or gather
any information
from you.
That's not...
that's not what I'm...
I just wanted you guys to go
into this thing knowing however
we vote is not going
to be easy
for us, because we
like all of y'all.
- Right. I'm not taking
anything personal, and if y'all
vote for me, that's cool.
I mean, that's part of the game,
that's part of the game.
I'm totally prepared for it.
- All right.
- They are very likely to vote
for me, and that's fine.
I mean, I'm not going
to lose sleep about it.
I'm not going to lose sleep
about it anymore.
If we could just do the thing
tonight, it's going to be me,
and I can beat him, okay?
We were talking about going to
Tribal Council, and Kelly was
standing on
the other side of
the hut and we didn't
realize it.
So now Lindsey thinks that they
know she has votes.
- She heard everything.
Positive.
She went right over to Big Bear,
and they started talking.
I just, I can't believe that
Brandon didn't whisper, and she
was standing right there.
- That may have
just... me.
- He's, like, "I'm going to
make it through this, it's okay,
da-da-da-da-da."
So they've got this plan, and
they sound like they've had it
for, like, two or three
days now.
- If that's the way they're
going to vote, that's the way
they're going to vote.
There's nothing
we can do.
- Yeah, there is
something we can do.
- What?
- Vote with them.
- Vote with them?
You know, we made a pact with
Brandon in the beginning of this
game, but he screwed me over by
letting them overhear that
I have votes,
so I was... I was upset.
So right now,
I feel like this
is a selfish game and I'm
in it for myself.
We're not
Samburu anymore.
- You know what I mean?
- So you guys are going to...
relinquish Brandon?
- Yeah, I mean,
I just feel so bad, like,
selling someone out,
but...
- Everyone would look
really positively at it.
- Let me think about it.
- Yeah, just think about it,
we can talk after lunch.
Okay, that's fine.
- I just thought, oh, my God,
if this can secure them not
voting for me, I'll do it,
and this isn't cheating.
I'm not sticking
a card up my sleeve.
This is just making the right
move for myself.
So what if we vote against
Brandon, then what happens?
- It sounds like a kind of
a merger to me.
- And if we don't?
- Well, if not, it's going to
hurt everybody later.
- They're basically saying
align with us, we'll take you
further, and I'm just not
going to do it.
I'm not comfortable with it.
I know Brandon
wouldn't do it to me.
He wouldn't do it to me,
no matter what.
- I'm kind of in a no-win
situation.
I mean, do I go against my
personal morals and values
and vote against Brandon?
Or do I vote with Brandon and
Kim and risk being the next one
voted out of here?
I don't know what I'm going to
do, and I don't think I'll know
until I get to Tribal Council.
- How's it going, guys?
First time we've
had this configuration
here at Tribal
Council.
Lex, take me back to when you
had this new tribe formed.
How is that working out?
- It was a real shocker to
begin with, but I think we've
all acclimated pretty well.
We've kind of
come together as a tribe,
which makes a night like
tonight pretty tough.
- (Probst) Brandon,
at this point,
do you trust
these other five?
- I think that
as far as trust goes,
you don't trust anybody
in the game.
It's just, it's a fact of life,
one of us has to go,
and it may be me, may be
somebody else, we'll just see.
- (Probst) Kim, is this game
more ethically challenging
than you anticipated?
- Yes. I think that you either
decide that you're going to play
this for me, and I'm going to
get myself to be number one and
as far as I can, or you decide
I'm going to do this with value
and integrity and all of my own
ethics, and I don't think
that there's
a middle road anywhere.
- (Probst) Kelly, what started
out as Samburu and Boran,
are those
tribes just gone now?
- I wouldn't say they're
just gone.
Obviously, you know, we...
we're very close with some of
the people that were on Boran,
and we still have
loyalties to them,
but it just really opened up our
eyes that these people
are great,
and it's really changed up
the game in a lot of ways.
It's made everything
a lot harder.
- It's time to vote.
Brandon,
you're up first.
- (whispering) I hate having
to vote for this person.
I'd rather vote for myself right
now, 'cause this is miserable.
- I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Big Tom.
Lindsey.
Tom.
- Hey.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay. Stop it.
It's me. Go.
- (Probst) Lindsey.
- Guys, it's a game!
- (Probst) Lindsey,
where are you going?
Sit it.
- (laughing)
- (Probst) That's three votes
Lindsey, three votes Tom.
We're going to vote again.
- Okay.
- (Probst)
But before we vote,
I'm going to give you guys
a chance to plead your case.
You're fighting for your life in
this game right now.
Be convincing.
Tom, you first.
- Well, only thing I can say
is, I'm who I am, I'm nobody
different, and I'm not
going to change.
So... that's... you got Big Tom
here, and that's the way it is.
- Lindsey, obviously tribal
lines coming into play here.
This is a chance for you to turn
somebody's vote around.
- Um, all I really want to say
is that I came to Tribal Council
tonight thinking, um,
the majority of them were going
to vote for Brandon,
and I considered it.
I considered joining with them
and voting for Brandon.
And on the way here, um...
(voice breaking)
...my dignity took over.
I don't care if I'm voted out
tonight, because I didn't vote
for a friend of mine, and that
makes me the happiest person on
the face of the Earth.
So I'm not
going to convince you
to keep me, 'cause I'm leaving
with my pride.
That's all.
- (Probst) Obviously, a tough
vote for you guys.
I believe that.
We got to do it again.
Lindsey and Tom,
you won't vote this time.
The other four of you will,
and you have to vote, obviously,
for Tom or for Lindsey.
I'll go tally the votes.
I'll read the re-vote.
First vote...
Big Tom.
Tom.
Lindsey.
And we're deadlocked.
Well, as you guys know, Tribal
Council is a place where you
account for your actions.
In the case of a deadlock,
we go to votes cast at previous
Tribal Councils.
Tom, how many votes have
you had cast against you?
- None that I know of.
- (Probst) Lindsey?
- A couple.
- (Probst) Four?
- Maybe.
- (Probst)
That's enough.
You need to bring me
your torch.
- Oh, stop it.
(speaking inaudibly)
It's okay.
It's a game, guys.
You're the best.
- I love you, too.
- Lindsey,
the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Good night.
- Bye.
- We'll miss you.
- Well, clearly, in spite of
what was said tonight,
tribal lines still playing a big
part, because this was the most
emotional Tribal Council I think
we've ever had.
You guys can
head back to camp.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
- (Probst) Next time on
Survivor...
The tribes eagerly anticipate
the traditional merge,
but anxieties run high.
- It is absolutely
horrible.
- (Probst) Because no one knows
how or when it will happen.
- Kind of like
standing on a corner
and the bus didn't
come by.
- Wake up, wake up.
Yo, we got mail.
It is big
and it is nasty.
- Tonight's vote was a
surprise.
I thought that they
would vote for Brandon.
I honestly don't think I could
have gone on much longer,
because this game is a serious
emotional roller coaster ride.
And, you know, I'm an athlete,
but I'd much rather do it in a
civilized environment, where I'm
not battling malicious behavior.
I don't like that aspect
of this game at all.
See you on the dark side.