>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
At Samburu, the gap between
young and old widened when Silas
took sides with his own
generation.
>> Straddling the fence is over.
I am no longer with the older
people, and I don't care if they
know that.
>> 'Cause they're immature,
they're trying to get under
their skin, and it's working.
>> PROBST: Boran rebounded from
their losing streak, winning
their first reward challenge.
Then they bared all to claim
immunity, sending Samburu to
their first Tribal Council,
where the young-old split caused
a deadlock tie between Lindsey
and Carl.
With no previous votes between
them to break the tie, a sudden-
death competition sent Carl
packing.
>> PROBST: True.
The tribe has spoken.
And Lindsey returned to camp
with four votes.
13 are left.
Tonight, one more will go.
♪ ♪
>> All right, make that fire
big.
>> Big fire.
Torches by the flag.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, we had our first Tribal
Council.
We voted Doc off.
All eight of us went in there
and split four and four.
>> I am still here and I am
smiling big.
>> Anything could've happened.
It was literally a crapshoot.
Whoever won, uh, won that Tribal
Council basically won the
majority, and basically more or
less took over the tribe.
>> Here's the deal.
If you guys want to go to the
water hole or whatever, we
understand that.
But, I mean, just, you know, let
us know, and we'll go-- we'll
either go as a group or you guys
can go.
>> And the people that get up
right away need to just be
patient for those that need a
little extra sleep, that may
have stayed up a little bit
later.
>> By the time I got back to
camp I felt really angry, just
like, it all hit me just like,
oh, my God, they picked me,
those bastards!
You know? And I just got really
angry and I just wanted to lash
out and just be mad at those
three people for voting for me.
Seriously pumped to get an award
tomorrow.
Seriously pumped, and trust me,
when I'm pumped you don't want
to ... with me.
Don't underestimate me, people.
>> The thing about Lindsey, of
course she handled it wrong.
We needed their support and we
needed to be kind to them, but,
boy, she really just kind of
flew off, you know, the deep
end.
>> Trust me.
>> It was difficult hearing
comments when they came back,
like Lindsey was saying,
"They ... with the wrong girl,"
and comments like, "Okay, so
come here, team," and they
really meant the four of them.
>> Tomorrow morning we are like
a full-on team again.
So let's just have one more
moment.
>> It was no accident because I
was standing right there where
Silas was over by the fire, and
they got him, and I thought, oh,
God... that's mean.
>> Tomorrow is a new day.
>> It can be.
It's got to be.
>> It don't got to be, I mean,
it can be.
>> Now it's a new day.
Yeah, sure, we're outnumbered
four to three, but basically
they run the show, you know.
But, uh... damn you, Carl, for
leaving me with a bunch of
misfits, you know, to go camping
with, 'cause it's gonna be
pretty miserable the next couple
of days.
>> Day ten.
>> Day ten. Let's win.
>> Yeah.
>> How's it looking?
>> Looks like we don't have as
much as we thought we had.
>> But it was very generous in
the beginning.
>> Very good.
>> Breakfast is served.
Breakfast of champions.
>> You know, I worry about
Tommy.
Tommy's not eating.
A lot of what we have to eat is
cornmeal, and he has a really
tough time eating it.
I don't think it's a taste
thing.
He just... he physically just
doesn't like the way it goes
down.
All it is really is just grits.
Like you would serve it with
breakfast.
>> Well, grits is a nice thought
for this stuff, but going down
the hatch, it reminds you more
of something rhymes with grits.
But... basically no grits.
We've got to find a little
something we can munch on.
>> Let's start with the fruit.
>> Can you hit that?
>> I can hit that.
>> You sure you can hit that?
>> Hell, yes, I... You watch me.
>> The big country bear saw the
palm trees.
The palm trees have what's
called a dome palm fruit on it.
The palm tree that Tommy found
was about 50 feet in the air.
(laughs)
He was silly enough to think he
was going to climb it.
>> Tommy, Tommy.
Hell, no, hell no!
Get down, man!
Tommy... T... Tommy.
Your big country ass is climbing
a tree in the middle of Africa.
You realize that, don't you?
>> What?
>> You come down.
Come down, you don't have no
safety harnesses.
I thought he was nuts.
Dawg.
(laughs): He's silly as hell.
So finally he got down, and we
just started throwing rocks at
it trying to get something to
happen.
>> All right, brother, rock and
roll here.
>> Watch your head!
>> Damn, Tommy!
And, uh, we actually got two of
them down.
>> Look it, palm!
>> And then after that, we've
hammered ourselves to death
trying to get the doggoned thing
open.
>> Looks like you're getting a
nice slice there.
>> Throwing for over 30 minutes,
getting two, then taking 20
minutes to open one-- we had
something about the size of your
thumb there that you could eat.
>> (gasps)
>> In my opinion, it ain't worth
it.
>> I mean, it's not as good as
coconut.
It's got a bad aftertaste.
>> I ain't mentioned it to Linda
and Teresa.
I said I was taking it out of
fifth gear as far as
responsibility, you know,
accountability, organizing
things, and I was going to sit
back.
They were the majority-- let's
see how they run a household.
>> Let's see what we have now.
>> When Frank and I got mail
this morning, I was loving it.
Oh, yeah, that was great.
I thought, if anything that will
drill in that you can't just
sleep late.
Our water is low.
Now, we don't have time to get
to the water hole.
Hey, guys, hate to wake you up.
We got mail!
And we got 30 minutes.
>> Oh, my God.
>> We were sleeping late, and
Linda had gotten tree mail, and
came up and woke us and said we
had half an hour to go to our
reward challenge, which was just
huge and shocking.
So we'd all gotten up and were
all groggy and very cranky.
>> Who would like to read this?
>> You read it. You read it.
>> No, no, no.
Why don't one of you read it?
>> "You'll have to decide how
high..."
>> Go on. You got it.
>> "...you should climb.
But if your team's better and
quick, like a spider, you'll be
celebrating as your bellies get
wider."
>> Oh!
>> Yeah! Rise and shine!
It's a beautiful day.
>> Let's make it happen, team.
>> It's a food reward.
>> It's hot already.
>> Anybody hungry?
>> We tried to sleep in, and we
got... we were awakened and now
we're struggling to get our
bearings.
>> All right, guys, this is a
reward, baby, this is a big 'un.
Frank, come here. Linda...
Hey, you guys come here for a
second.
Come here, Frank, for just a
second, man.
You guys, you know what, dad-
gummit, man, I know last night
was a... you know, we went in
there 50-50.
I realize the situation right
now, guys.
Let's come together right now as
a team.
I mean, this is... we're so
unorganized right now, you know.
And we're so... we're so...
>> Still.
>> Silas, with the knee, I've
seen him on the knee twice, and
I looked at that, and I guess, I
don't know, that's like a
football thing where the coach
gets down and just whatever.
Maybe it's genuine.
It seemed so cheesy to me.
>> Let's get fired up here and
win this.
>> Could I make one suggestion?
>> Please, please do. Please.
>> If, um, there were several
things last night that were
stated, and what that did, that,
you know, we were all willing to
do this, totally willing to do
this...
>> I know.
>> ...and that made it go...
>> You have to understand this,
though, too, Linda.
>> That's all.
>> What if that was you on the
cutting board?
>> There's no way I would have
come back and said to the three
people, "Hey, team, team, come
here," and there's no way I
would have said, with that girl,
"Revenge, revenge."
There's no way I would have
disrespected any of you that
way, no way.
Kim, you know.
>> It's over.
We're coming together now.
It's over.
>> It's over and out.
>> Thank you!
>> So, I'm sorry that... I'm
sorry that it happened.
>> You know...
>> Yeah, we got to go.
I've been dying to be on this
team!
Let me on the team!
>> Linda, this morning, really
came unglued.
She has two very, very different
sides.
It's, like, this sweet little
New England mom, and then
there's this, I don't know,
crazy-woman side, too.
>> You know, I'm ready to be on
the team!
Ready to be on the team, honey.
Could I have a hug!
See? You're even hesitating.
Give me a hug.
You know... why can't you hug
me?
>> I hugged you.
>> Frank? Come on, Frank.
>> Can I... can we demonstrate a
hug?
This is a hug, sweetie.
Did your mama never hug you?
There you go.
>> They were saying, oh, it was
just 'cause anger and, like, let
it go.
I'm, like, okay, great, let it
go, let's hug.
And arms went like this, and she
has... she got that look in
her eyes, like, like, I don't
know, I had a knife in my hand
or she was gonna... it was...
it was awfully strange.
Why don't you give me a real
hug?
>> It was hard.
It's hard, you know?
>> Okay, you're not ready to, I
understand, I respect that.
>> I saw a side to you that...
>> I totally respect that.
>> ...I'm really nervous about.
>> Well, you know what anger is?
Anger is a cover-up for sadness.
Whenever we're angry...
>> Well, I'm good at it, Linda.
>> Sadness, just get there.
>> Well, it's funny, I think,
it's... if, you know, no matter
if it went...
>> (crying): Don't tell me
it's all right.
>> Just trying, just trying.
But I respect your space.
>> Just everything sort of hit
me this morning, and I just
started to cry, because I felt
just... I felt sectioned out of
my little group, even though
they're totally supportive of
me.
I felt like the older group
picked me, and how can I face
them again, and I just felt sad.
(sniffles)
>> PROBST: Good morning, guys.
How's the cornmeal taste?
Getting a little bland?
>> Getting?
(laughter)
>> PROST: It was bland to begin
with.
All right, hopefully we can do a
little something about that
today.
Today's challenge is a food
reward.
Behind us on a rope web, 12
items that will dramatically
improve your meals.
Things like olive oil, sun-dried
tomatoes.
>> Ooh...
>> PROBST: So a big food reward.
Here's how it works.
One at a time, tribe members
are gonna make their way up the
ramp, across the netting and up
the rope web.
They are going to grab one item
and bring it back.
Once you cross the line the next
person goes.
The first tribe to get all items
back in their basket wins the
food reward.
Losers get squat.
Make sense?
Wait for my go.
Here we go, guys.
Survivors, ready!
>> (whoops)
>> Go!
>> Go! Go, baby!
(cheering, shouting)
(groaning)
(grunts)
(gasps)
>> Whoa!
>> Go! Go!
(whooping, whistling)
>> Come on!
Come on, Clarence!
(indistinct shouts)
>> Come on, girl.
>> Good job!
(whooping)
>> Let's go!
>> Let's go, team!
Come on, team!
(indistinct shouts)
>> Go!
(whooping)
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> Go, Linda!
Come on, Frank!
(whooping)
>> Let's go, Frank!
>> PROBST: Okay, guys, get ready
for your second run.
You're still neck and neck.
>> Go, B.!
>> Go!
(indistinct shouts, whistling)
(grunts)
>> Go, go, go, climb!
It's not like you've never
climbed before!
>> Go, T-bird!
>> PROBST: All right, guys,
you're still even.
(indistinct shouts)
>> Come on!
>> Come on, Kimmy!
(whooping, shouting)
>> Let's go, let's go!
(indistinct shout)
>> Go, Lindsey!
(whooping)
(whistling)
(indistinct shouts)
(whooping, whistling continue)
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> Come on, Kimmy!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Samburu, this is your
last basket.
Boran, you still got two.
>> Yeah!
>> Samburu!
>> PROBST: Samburu, a lot of
stuff in there.
Take your prize home, have a
good meal.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for
immunity.
All right, see you guys.
>> We lost the challenge.
Unfortunately, you know, it came
down to Kim went really slow.
I feel terrible for her.
She couldn't feel good, and I
know she doesn't feel good, and
it's hard, it must be really...
I'm glad I'm not in that
situation.
>> Sorry, not a great job.
Well, also, I mean, I don't like
to be that terrible at
something.
That's, like...
>> No one does.
>> That's, like, really
terrible.
>> You know, we all fell, we all
took our time, every one us took
fell down.
>> We all said, you know, "Good
job, you did the best you
could," but, you know, really,
she was, like, "I suck," and
we're, like, "Yeah, you... you
suck."
>> I could tell from your faces
everybody gave it 100%.
>> You know, in competition it's
not about giving it your best
sometimes; sometimes it's about
actual... the winning.
>> We just got to, got to hope
we get out there and get them
next time.
>> Let's just drink the water.
>> I wonder what immunity is
going to be.
>> I don't know.
>> The thing that was most
difficult about today's
challenge was my having to face
the reality that Kim is
definitely not up to some of the
more physical challenges.
>> There's nothing good about
losing, like, nothing.
>> If our team is just real
losers and we lose everything,
that's going to be awful.
>> All right!
(whooping)
>> This morning was a little
tense, but we really pulled
together today and we won some
food.
All in all, it was an
unbelievable victory today.
So it boosted up morale, boosted
spirits, boosted everything,
confidence-- it was a good
thing.
Let's pull them out one at a
time and tell me what it is.
>> We've got...
golden chicken blend.
>> Nice.
>> Spice?
>> Ooh, to put in the mush.
>> Olive oil!
(gasps)
>> Yeah, olive oil.
>> The basket we won was just
amazing.
We won soup mix, you know, rice,
we won, like, jelly to put on
stuff.
I mean, it's flavor, for the
food that we have, and that's
key.
(speaking indistinctly)
>> I cannot be any more excited
about the fact we got food,
unless it was water.
(laughs)
I would give it all up for
water.
>> Should we do a water run,
right now?
>> Right now.
>> We're going to have a heck of
a hike, though-- we're carrying
all three big gourds...
>> We'll go slow.
>> ...all the water gourds.
Load up.
>> We can take some rests, I
think, 'cause...
>> Sure.
>> One of the big focuses in our
group is water, obviously.
We have to go get the water, we
have to boil the water.
Frank and Doc were kind of the
two people who took it under
their wing, they were kind of
the water people, getting the
water going.
And our group was going...
and they were doing all the
work.
Fine with us; we don't do any of
it.
We were more focused on the
split in the tribe and
manipulating people and doing
that than we were about any
other part of surviving out
here.
>> You fill this one, then you
take a breather, I'll fill this,
and we'll rotate the fillers
here.
Because I know, you know, you
and Linda usually fill these
things, and we'll rotate.
>> That's cool.
>> We were in a real water
crunch.
I mean, we were all dehydrated
from the challenge severely.
And I'm sure to prove a point to
us, Frank and Linda and T let
the water level get...
completely gone.
>> Come on, guys, last leg.
We're almost there.
>> We're just going...
>> Then we came home,
lost another pot completely.
Pots are extremely valuable,
because that's the only way we
have to have clean drinking
water.
We have to boil it.
>> Is it leaking right now?
>> Yeah.
>> Yep.
>> One of our pots now is
completely unusable and the
other one, you know, is still on
its side and just, it's
crumbling.
Every time we put it in the fire
it crumbles more and more.
>> Let's fill it up.
Who's got a gourd?
>> Things began to slack off.
You know, the water rations went
down.
My plan of attack was, you know,
to let the comfort level drop
completely low, and they
would...
I know they would break down.
And, uh, you could see that
things were falling apart.
>> Oh, my gosh.
Guys, we're in a heap of
trouble.
>> Can you save the bottom?
Can you save it where it's
leaking out?
>> Hold that side.
>> You ready?
>> Let's see if we can lift it.
Lift it off the ground.
Right there.
>> We now have completely
shattered all of our pots.
So it's a horrible situation
that we got ourselves into.
>> Huh.
>> We are not in good shape,
boys and girls, I'll just say
that right now.
>> We'll make due, we'll make
due.
>> I'm still, like, God, this
tribe, can we get our act
together?
You know, there's still that
hanging over my head, like...
what's wrong with us?
You know, we crack pots, we
whine, we complain, we have
problems, people are fighting,
da-da-da-da, whatever, and I'm
like, God, when are we going to
get this together?
(screeching)
>> What's up ahead, Tom?
>> Baboons.
Looks like a pretty good tribe
of them.
>> Best thing we can do is just
let them go.
They let us go.
We're starting to be animal-
friendly.
Whatever they want, we'll do.
>> Sometimes you do get
comfortable, a little bit
comfortable here, and, you know,
you think you're all safe and
everything's great.
And then you get a wake-up call.
(whistling)
>> Buffalo.
>> Tom had his eyes up, thank
God.
>> Stand there.
>> We've all done our homework,
and we all know that that is the
one animal that we need to be
most careful of.
It's considered to be the most
dangerous animal in Africa.
>> You don't mess with this, you
guys, you know?
>> It was scary.
It was there and it was huge.
So when we saw this thing, we
made a lot of noise.
>> Ho!
(whistling)
>> And then we realized at that
point we needed to leave this
place.
>> All right, guys, let's go.
>> You want to head a little
left, Tommy?
>> You all in agreement that we
should go a little bit fur...
left?
>> I can still see him, too.
I don't want to move.
>> I don't think we should move,
either.
>> He's coming right towards
camp.
>> We're not in a hurry.
>> Not a single one of us came
here thinking that all of this
danger was going to be real.
>> Our camp's right over there
to the left.
>> We're finding on a daily
basis, we're having these
kind of sobering experiences
that remind us every day that we
need to respect the land, and
that this whole thing is very
real.
Danger is here.
>> Bad-tempered.
>> Bad neighbors.
>> Good morning, camp Samburu.
Rise and shine.
Don't plug in the curling irons.
There ain't no beauty contest
this morning, just a little
watering hole expedition.
(groaning)
This morning I took a long shot.
First thing before the sun even
got up, I got them up.
The water thing I can't ignore.
Believe me, if it was just me
and them, I'd let them fall flat
on their faces, 'cause I don't
give a damn, you know?
But I can't do that to Teresa
and Linda.
I feel compelled to, you know,
want to protect and make life
easy for them as well.
You can take a nice little
morning hike.
Get it out of the way.
While it's nice and cool, all
right?
>> All right.
>> Come on, guys.
>> Frank, we just hit the snooze
button.
>> Oh don't tell me you guys are
the snooze button type of
people.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Oh, you don't need a snooze
button.
You've been sleeping most of
your lives.
Come on, it's getting hot
already.
>> Who-who agreed on this?
Who, uh...
>> Shut up. Shut up.
(elephant trumpeting)
>> My ass is on the line here,
you know.
>> It's not... I mean...
>> I know, I know, it's a
team...
>> We'll just buy you a little
more time...
>> I know. Then we don't have...
>> one more challenge, then you
don't have to worry about it.
"Living like nomads means moving
around.
Do well at this challenge, you
may stick around.
Now if you fall behind and the
other tribe wins, it's immunity
for them as your hike to Council
begins."
It is physical, but I'm sure you
have to do... smarts with it,
too.
It isn't just brute, like
pushing a rock.
>> PROBST: All right, first
thing I need to do-- take back
the immunity idol.
Give it up, Clarence.
(laughter)
Immunity back at stake again
today.
For today's immunity challenge,
we're going to look to our
African hosts for a little
inspiration.
The tribes of East Africa are
nomadic, thus they are
constantly relocating their
camp.
That's what you guys are going
to do today.
Each tribe has a camp with a
hut, an animal pen, flagpole,
and various camp supplies.
First tribe to relocate their
camp up to your new home, 200
yards up the hill, and recreate
it exactly as it is here, wins
immunity.
Here are the rules.
Two members from each tribe will
be your architects.
Their job is to remember how the
camp looks here and to make sure
that it gets recreated exactly
the same way in your new home.
They will not help move the
camp.
They will be up at the new
location.
And they can only help you
rebuild once your pieces have
been placed inside your circle.
The other members will be
responsible for actually
physically relocating the camp.
Last rule.
The flagpole is the last thing
you put in.
Samburu, because you guys are
still one member ahead, somebody
is sitting out.
Once you've made that decision,
send that person with your
architects to the top of the
hill.
All right, Samburu, you're
sitting out Teresa.
Brandon and Linda will be your
architects.
Boran, you've selected Kelly and
Kim as your architects.
All right, architects are in
place at the top of the hill.
Immunity at stake.
Survivors, ready!
Go!
>> Go, go, go!
>> Lift it up, lift it up.
(indistinct shouts)
>> Let's go!
I got it. Lift it up.
>> Make it steady up the hill!
You guys are doing awesome!
>> Take your time.
>> Just go! Move it.
(indistinct talking)
>> Come on, let's go.
>> Turn. Turn.
Come on, turn.
Back it up, back it up.
Down. 'Kay, yeah.
Little back this way.
>> Move, Frank! Move!
>> Let's go!
>> Drop, drop, drop, drop it.
(indistinct shouts)
>> Lift it up.
>> What about the basket?
>> Wait, wait, wait!
>> Come on! You're doing great!
>> Your pace is excellent!
>> Let's go!
Kim, get on it, use your
shoulders.
>> I have it!
>> Excellent work.
(indistinct shouts)
(indistinct shouts continue)
>> You got to go ack, back,
back. Okay.
(shouts continue)
>> PROBST: Boran all you have
left are your roof and your
flag.
Samburu you still need the walls
to your hut.
>> That goes over here.
>> Ready?
Come on, Tommy.
(indistinct shouts continue)
>> I got it!
(panting loudly)
>> I don't know where I'm going,
so lead me to victory, guys!
>> Turn left.
Girls, help with the huts.
>> Okay.
>> All right.
>> Up, up, up, yeah, you guys
are doing great.
>> Up!
Up!
>> Lift! Lift!
>> (yells)
>> Somebody help straighten it.
>> No pegs; just set it in
there.
>> Just set it in.
>> PROBST: The house is good.
>> House is good!
>> Drop it! Drop it, drop it.
>> PROBST: Everybody in the
circle before you put that flag
in, Tom.
Boran!
(cheering)
(indistinct talking)
>> Good job, guys!
>> PROBST: Boran keeps immunity!
Congratulations, guys.
(cheering, whooping)
(indistinct shouts)
>> Oh, my gosh, you guys are
awesome.
>> PROBST: See you guys tomorrow
night at Tribal Council.
>> Happy birthday.
>> Oh, thank you, sweetie.
Happy Birthday.
>> This morning, Frank's
birthday, got up, gave him a
birthday hug, and he was
whittling on his torch, and he
was carving his children and his
wife's name.
I thought that was just
beautiful.
>> I grabbed my Tribal Council
torch, and I wanted my wife and
two daughters, Josyln and Sage's
name to be on that, for not
only now, the strength, but even
when I leave, you know, I want
it to be carried with me.
They were with me all the time.
So it was important for me to do
that.
>> I'll tell you one thing.
We could have used Carl
yesterday.
We might have won. Oh, yeah.
I bet you tactically they were
wondering about that.
But I think you can get some
mileage, Frank.
If you fly low, you can get
there.
>> If I get there I think I'm
going to go behind enemy lines.
>> Are you?
>> Just to stir things up.
>> It's nice to be walking
someplace for fun, isn't it?
>> What a change, what a
difference.
>> We kicked ass in that
challenge and we won, and it
saved Kim's life.
>> Words can't express how happy
I am.
I mean, I could just stand here
and cry.
I'm so happy.
And the thing that makes me
really happy...
is that I think they're all
happy about it, even personally,
for me.
>> We've won immunity, and the
other team is going to Tribal
Council, so we have to whole day
to ourselves, no chores, so we
decided to explore a little bit.
When our tribe climbed up that
mountain, you know, I got that
feeling back about why, what was
really important and why I was
there.
Everyone is happy and the tribe
is happy, and we're all having
fun.
And it was just so pleasant, it
was like... we're here, like,
we're in Africa.
>> Tribe, you've seen the
promised land.
>> It's obviously D day.
Um, we go to Tribal Council this
evening.
We know it's either going to be
myself, T or Frank that's going
to go.
>> I wish it had been me who had
been voted for, because it
wouldn't have bothered me at
all.
>> I was just kind of sitting
there relaxing, and everyone
started opening up very
neutrally and casually.
>> I think tonight will be
better.
I think we're calmer.
>> Yeah.
>> And we understand what's
going on a little bit better,
and I won't be voted out.
(laughs)
>> So who's going tonight,
since we're so open?
>> Yeah, I like that.
>> Well, hey, I know this sounds
crazy.
We know it's one of us.
Wouldn't you rather know if it's
gonna be you?
>> We're not gonna tell you.
>> Just hold off, because
I agree with Brandon.
Let me just throw this out.
>> I don't want this day to be
bad.
>> Let me throw this out.
And I don't want the day to be
bad anyway.
But let's just be real here that
we're playing the game.
Lindsey already has four votes
against her.
If you ever go into Tribal
Council with a tie, like myself
and someone else, the
tiebreaker who has the most
votes is out.
None of us have one vote against
us, not one.
>> Except for Lindsey.
>> Except for Lindsey-- this is
the key.
>> As of this moment.
>> This is the key.
>> I never thought I'd say,
"Vote for me three times
tonight. Come on!"
But it will help us, it'll help
us in the end, as long as I
don't get voted for, you know,
once the merger happens.
>> Whoever is being voted off
tonight should vote for Lindsey.
>> And what's in it for us?
>> Nothing.
>> Please stick with us on this,
and just think about it, and
vote for Lindsey.
>> I'll be honest, I care, but,
like, if I'm the person who's
going this evening, I'm not
going to do that.
Because there's totally nothing
in it for me.
>> Well, they wouldn't say who's
going tonight, but they had a
plan they wanted us to follow--
you know, us now.
It's just, it's funny, that's
all.
>> Would you rather bring the
whole ship down with you, or
would you rather save your ship?
>> The whole ship is not coming
down.
>> That's the point, Linda.
>> I do not want to see Silas
win the million dollars.
I can see any of the other three
win the million dollars, but I
don't want him winning the
million dollars.
I don't trust him at all.
There's something, there's
something up there.
I'm not even sure of his name.
There's just something not quite
right.
>> One of the three of you has
to go. I mean...
>> I don't know, Frank and Linda
how do you guys feel?
If I'm going, I'd rather know.
>> The minute we told you and we
were about to be honest with
you, you said, "What's in it for
me?"
So why in the world would we
go ahead and finish?
That was a bitter taste in
the mouth right there.
>> I really don't know which way
they're going, but I guess
there's a reason they could keep
each one of us and a reason they
could decide to take each one of
us off.
>> Let's drop this.
Let's drop this.
>> There's not an event in the
future that would alarm me.
I can't wait until the merge
because I plan on winning this.
You might as well write the
check and hand it to me, because
I'm shooting for the stars,
and-and... I'm going to get
there.
>> PROBST: Well, guys, back for
a second time in a row.
Let's go back to the first time
you were here.
Pretty intense dialogue was had.
When you went back to camp that
night, was there any of the
bonding that you guys talked
about making the tribe one
again?
>> The first night, you know,
there was some emotional times
right after the Council.
Feelings were hurt, you know.
None of us know how it feels
except Lindsey to get a vote
against you, and so that was
hard, Jeff.
But after that, the second day,
much better.
We came together as a unit.
>> PROBST: Frank, after the last
immunity challenge, you guys
knew you were coming back to
Tribal Council.
What happened when you went back
to camp?
What was the tone of the tribe?
Were you guys concerned?
>> Well, obviously the three of
us, you know, we knew one of us
would be going.
>> PROBST: The three of you,
referring to Linda and Teresa?
>> To Linda, Teresa and myself.
There are two tribes within one
still.
>> PROBST: It's surprising to
me, because it's the first time
I've ever seen this.
I'm trying to figure out where
the logic to this is, because
going into a merge, you need
numbers.
>> Is there a sure thing in this
whole game, Jeff?
Can you tell me one sure thing
about this whole entire game?
>> PROBST: I can tell you...
>> Just one.
>> PROBST: Yeah, I can tell you
one sure thing.
If Samburu goes into a merge
with four people solid and one
not solid, and Boran goes in
with five people solid, Samburu
is in trouble.
That I can tell you for certain.
>> Jeff, you need to take into
consideration, if I wasn't here
tonight...
>> There we go.
>> ...one of us would be going.
It would be the same thing.
It would be the exact same thing
but reversed.
>> PROBST: Frank, anything you
can do to turn this game around
at this point?
>> Oh, there's always something
to do.
It's just waiting for the proper
opening, you know, to happen.
>> PROBST: So you have a game
plan?
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: You're sticking to
it?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: Lindsey, have you
made any mistakes so far,
anything that...?
>> Oh, tons.
I'm a walking mistake.
>> You know, when you hear
things-- "Oh, you're the one
that's next," "No, Kim's next,"
"Oh, no, it's Brandon," you
panic, and I brought some
negative energy to the group
because I was frustrated and fed
up, and I freaked out about the
whole manipulative process and
the panic attacks and the
feelings of anxiety like you're
the one that's going to go next,
and, you know, you lose sight of
reality because it's not
reality.
It's just a game and we're
trying to keep that in
perspective, and I'm awful at it
because I'm sensitive, I get my
feelings hurt.
>> PROBST: Brandon, have you
ever taken a walk by yourself
and thought, "Okay, wait a
minute..."
>> I don't do anything by
myself-- I'm always with them.
Always. I'm always with them.
These are my friends.
Even aside from the game,
they're my friends.
I'm not changing my mind on any
of that.
Yeah, definitely.
>> PROBST: It's time to vote.
Lindsey, you're first.
>> It's a game...
and it's your time to go.
>> Well, buddy, this is for
Carl, for Frank and for Teresa.
It's only a game.
Play nicely.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Silas.
Three votes Silas.
Linda.
Three votes Silas, three votes
Final vote.
Linda.
You need to bring me your torch.
(speaking quietly)
>> Play nicely.
>> PROBST: Linda...
the tribe has spoken.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: It's time for you to
go.
>> Bye guys.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: Well, one very clear
result of this split within your
own tribe is that, Lindsey, you
now have four votes against you,
Silas you have three votes.
That's a lot of votes after only
two Tribal Councils.
Could most definitely come into
play in future votes.
>> No doubt.
>> We know very well.
>> PROBST: I'll leave you with
this final thought.
Silas, you said it best: this
game changes minute by minute.
It certainly does.
You guys can head back to camp.
I'll see you tomorrow.
>> Well, it's been an
interesting 12 days.
I think our vote tonight, the
older people's alliance, is
a very significant honor.
It's very important to us.
Integrity is very important to
us.
To me, it's not whether you win
or lose, it's how you play the
game.
I've grown, I've learned.
It's just been great.
Namaste.