Previously on Survivor:
Maraamu found a new source of food...
and won a crucial reward challenge
that allowed them to sack Rotu's camp.
Maraamu, prepare to loot.
It was great. We took everything.
... and that brought Rotu even closer together.
Everyone felt they had a role in the tribe.
But the unit faltered
when John became suspicious of Gabe's behavior.
Are we still united?
Is that the deal?
Little Maraamu also won her first immunity.
And John did what was necessary to embarrass Gabe.
Tomorrow we kick Gabe out.
Rotu went to his first Tribal Council,
where Rob followed the majority vote,
although he had a message for John.
I know exactly what you are trying to do.
As soon as I can, I'm coming for you.
And Gabe was kicked out of the tribe.
Gabe, the tribe has spoken.
11 remain.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
Spanish Subs & Synch by Moriarty Inc.
The original 4 Rotu, Zoe, myself, John and Tammy,
made a pact to try to control this
and take us to the bottom 4.
And right now, we're pretty confident we're in control.
I'm not talking bullshit.
I mean, if we get it right,
the winner will come out of this group.
I've been waiting to lose one
so we could, you know, get rid of Gabe....
My leadership has emerged since we kicked Gabe out.
It was a big change,
especially because now everyone knows that I am the leader.
Everyone knows that I pull the strings.
If we were to lose the next immunity challenge,
we would be 4 against 3.
And, to be honest, the reward challenge is what we really want.
is the one we really want.
No matter what it is,
we need the best people to participate.
And maybe not put so much effort and will
in the immunity that comes later.
John has proclaimed himself to be the powerhouse of our little
our little group.
Fine by me.
Right now, it's my turn to sit back, relax,
and let him eat the brown stuff.
He will be the target of the anger.
It will be my new tribal baptism, or whatever you want to call it,
but I got silly and went swimming in my balls.
Hey, Rob, I'm going to jump naked.
I was there with the original Rotu,
and after expelling Gabe,
it was like getting all that shit out of the way
and start all over again.
It was a very powerful moment.
Symbolically, it is like demonstrating another level in our relationship.
in our relationship.
I would not be comfortable doing it with the other 3.
Now the only chance we have is to hope to win immunity tomorrow.
is to hope to win immunity tomorrow,
and that there be a merger.
We have to work something out with the other side.
If not, we're out of here.
It's clear, they beat us 4-3.
By losing Gabe, we have lost a big advantage.
We know there are 4, we know there are 3.
We are going to be kicked out one by one.
And these little kisses...
And V. is clear that...
I don't know what you are about, but you are clearly and visibly distancing yourself from us.
clearly and visibly.
V. is driving me crazy,
because it's so clear what he's doing.
I do not trust V.
I have never trusted V.
I'll tell you one thing, Sean, my main goal is to get rid of him.
Because he thinks he's the dick.
If I get the slightest chance to kick John out,
I will take it.
I still don't have an angle.
I don't have a strategy yet,
but if I get the chance to kick him out,
will be the first to leave.
And if tomorrow we lose immunity,
yes, it will probably be you or me.
On this side there is more time to be quiet
because you don't have to work gathering food.
You have it at your fingertips.
Paschal, have you found anything?
yes, I see one.
Where there is one, there are more.
Physically, we are no competition
for the other team, and we know it.
But we take it as best we can.
Let's see, we do what we can,
and there is no need to think about it any more.
The mother of the lamb, look at this colleague!
- Do you have that side?
- I have this side.
Good job.
I used to worry about being in this little group of women with an older gentleman.
with an older gentleman,
and that it was going to be difficult to win.
But now that I'm here,
I see that it all comes down to spirit and energy and desire.
Oh, come here.
Where are those tweezers?
Oh, no, not at all!
Not at all.
You little bastard!
The mother who bore you!
He pinched me twice.
Fuck!
Oh, look at that.
Oh, my God.
No wonder it hurts to be pinched.
In Rotu we didn't eat as well
because there were more mouths to feed.
We are going to have to cook them right now.
We didn't eat in the morning, we didn't eat at noon,
we only had dinner.
That was great, Paschal.
I just waited for them to come out of the hole.
Yes, you have to wait for them to turn around.
Yes, control the time.
Well, we know where to come.
Here.
Good one, Kathy.
Yes.
If we win this one, as we are eating,
and knowing what they're eating...
Believe me, they are not eating.
I think they care more about food than immunity,
because they probably already have their alliance.
They already know who they are going to kick.
I can't wait to see which of the old guys got the boot.
It's going to be a stick for us
if it hasn't been one of your old ones,
because it seems to me that we all assume
that it's going to be one of two people.
I think it's going to be Rob,
others believe it will be Sean.
It will be interesting to find out who.
Guys, this is it.
Food on this side is much easier to find than in Rotu.
than in Rotu.
It's just amazing,
it's like night and day.
And it is very fresh.
We don't need food like they do,
that's for sure.
Let's see what we have today.
Sushi?
Oh, it's going to be food!
Yes, it is true.
"It's time to visit a mystical place.
The ideal place for your new career.
"Beyond land and sea, traveling a little further,
the first tribe sits down to dinner!
Yes!
They're not going to beat us by a long shot.
Not at all.
No way, and if there is food at the finish line,
that's motivation enough.
Rock and roll, people.
Gabe has been fired.
Oh!
Here in front, Rob.
Okay, let's go to our reward challenge.
It's a relay race through the jungle.
It goes like this.
Four members of each tribe will compete.
Relays have 3 parts.
In the first part, 1 of each tribe will run through the jungle until they find a paddle.
through the jungle to find a paddle.
It is tied with knots.
You will untie it and move on,
giving the baton to another of the tribe along the way.
You must go together.
The two of you will find another paddle that is tied up.
You will take the two oars to the second part,
which is a pile of coconuts.
There is a key hidden inside.
Start cracking coconuts until you find it.
Then pass the key and the oars to the other two tribe members.
two other tribe members.
In the third and last part,
these two members will use the key to open the canoe.
You will paddle away, take the flag,
turn around, paddle until you leave the canoe on the beach.
The canoe must be within reach of the chain.
The first tribe to have both paddlers on the tiki
in the tiki and places their flag wins the reward.
Do you want to know why you play?
Yes.
For starters, on a hot and humid day like today,
something cold, some Sierra Mist.
Oh, it's so cold, look.
A small sample of what awaits you.
Oh, my God.
Chicken, quiche, bean salad and a very tasty dessert.
Okay.
Rotu, since you have 7 members,
you have to seat 3.
Which 4 participate?
Okay, V., Sean, Tammy, you sit down.
The first two, head for the exit.
Wait for my signal.
Here we go, guys.
Survivors ready!
Go!
Take it easy, Rob!
Come on, Paschal!
Come on, sweetheart!
Well done, Paps!
Take it easy, Rob!
Good, Paps!
Come on, Paps, you got it!
- You want me to carry the paddle?
- I got it, I got it.
I see, here they have changed the knot.
They change in the middle.
Okay, Paps, are you ready?
This piece needs to be undone.
Come on, Paschal!
Come on, Rob.
Come on, you can do it!
Let's go.
Take your time.
Take your time, take your time.
Come on, Paschal!
The oar! The oar!
Okay, 1, 2, 3...
Let's go...
Rob, wait, wait, wait, wait.
One on one side, one on the other!
On my side, on my side.
Now rowing on the outside.
What are they doing?
I go on the inside, you go on the outside.
You still can, come on!
Come on, girls!
Drive, drive, you have to drive.
I row, you drive.
Drives.
Come on, girls, that's the way to do it!
Drive, drive, drive.
Good job, girls!
Rob, drive, don't paddle!
I am going to row.
Drives.
Put the oar in. There you go.
Good job, come on girls!
- Come on, come on, come on...
- Let's go!
Come on, Rotu!
Take it to the chain.
Take it to the chain!
Let's go, guys.
Push, push.
Run!
Get the flag!
Rotu!
- Rob wasn't there! Rob wasn't there.
- You're right.
It is true.
Rob was not there!
Just a moment, I have to check something.
Maraamu is protesting.
To win, your canoe had to be
within reach of the chain,
and the two rowers had to be in the tiki.
The canoe has to be within reach of the chain,
Maraamu's is fine.
Rotu...
does not arrive.
Besides, El General was not at the tiki when you put up the
you put up the flag.
I spoke too soon, sorry.
Rotu, you do not win.
Maraamu wins.
Feast.
Oh my God, it's a picnic!
Oh, my God, look at all the drinks!
Oh, my God, there's ice!
God, my hands are shaking.
Can I have another pair of Sierra Mists?
- What a mess.
- I can't believe it.
We can eat half each.
Oh, my God, it's a baguette.
Oh, jopé, guys, the chicken is amazing.
It's delicious! What's in it?
It's like a kind of pickle or something...
The challenge was very exciting.
It was definitely the reward we needed.
Not necessarily the food,
but to keep Rotu away from it.
I must have eaten 20 cookies.
No kidding.
Me too. We have to eat slowly,
so we can eat longer.
That is very difficult.
God, I feel terrible.
Why were they so grumpy?
Would we have been like this?
I have to say that this morning I couldn't believe it.
Oh, for Gabe? Flip-flopping.
- Absolutely amazing.
- Yes, I was flabbergasted.
Actually, when we were there,
Gabe was probably the strongest on the team,
I did everything.
Well, there's bound to be a lot of fighting over there.
I think the general opinion is that we feel like a family,
the four of us, I'm talking about a real family.
It is heaven on earth.
An old man like me with 3 women?
Does it get any better than that? No.
I love it when you say that.
It's going to make me throw up.
Yuck.
I'd rather you vomit.
We spend three-quarters of our time
fantasizing about food.
That's why it was a great, great disappointment
when they said we didn't win.
I'm sure their bellies will end up hurting
with so much food.
I hope that they will be able to eat as soon as they eat.
I won the race, I pissed on everyone.
I did my part.
I gave the key to Two Very Silly Fools,
and they proceeded to fuck up the rest of the race.
Maraamu is out there eating all kinds of yummy things.
And here we are, eating roots.
I don't mind so much that I lost the challenge.
For me, it's just a meal.
And I avoided asking for forgiveness,
because I'm in a leadership position,
and I'm not going to apologize for losing.
These people are going to go down in flames.
Those four are going to be sicker than a dog.
The food looked great.
But cucumbers, green peppers, and beans....
foods that give lots and lots of gas.
A lot of them. We would swell up in a second.
I would not have touched many of the things that were there.
2 hours of yum-yum would not make up for it,
you know, 3 days of... going for the heck of it.
That little meal means nothing.
There are 26 days left.
We didn't come here to eat fried chicken and quiche.
That's where you hit it.
We came here to play and to win,
and that is what we are going to do, period.
These are Tony Robbins' people, man.
Let's give it a go.
We have taro, we have coconuts.
It's an everyday thing, though,
we deceive ourselves
thinking that John is going to cook something new.
See what happens when you use your imagination?
What I do is cook the fish first,
then I pour the juice.
I kept some white pieces,
and I add the coconut, then the taro.
It's not too bad.
It's not fried chicken, but it's not bad.
A great recipe.
You have deceived me.
I still say the chicken would have been the bomb.
But here's the thing:
he says you would shit your pants.
What do we have here, apart from nature and occasions?
In the jungle, insects crawling,
in the hut of love, 8 friends sleeping,
We have fire, food and shelter,
water from the tropical storm,
And for the pigs, a vertical trap is prepared."
I don't recite as well as he does.
Gabe had written a poem to Paschal when they were in Rotu, the first 10 days.
when they were in Rotu, the first 10 days.
And Paschal and Gabe had a father-son relationship.
Paschal has no sons,
and he kept saying that, if he had a son, he'd love for him to be just like Gabe,
he'd love for it to be just like Gabe.
Can you return it to Paschal?
Thank you.
It is very special.
This morning, when I saw Rotu for the first time,
I was stunned.
And to tell you the truth, I was very disappointed,
because I know what it was like to be there and what Gabe had to offer.
23 years old. What a kid.
I still love the people there,
but it's different now.
Now we are who we are,
and that is in the past.
Oh... it makes me mad.
He shouldn't have left.
He was very talented.
Yes, he should not have been fired.
I knew it would break his heart,
when we saw that he didn't make it.
The mood of our tribe is very relaxed,
it's very peaceful.
And we're at a point where we can
just hang out.
Is it all in the breath?
Yes, it's breathing,
to get rid of stress.
And how long does this...?
Chi Kung.
Chi Kung?
Five minutes.
Kathy is great.
Kathy has a very good spirit.
It's a lot of go get 'em,
and probably more adventurous than me
What does that do to you?
It gets you in shape.
Oh, okay.
And now you can lie down on the couch,
turn on the soccer.
Open a beer.
Gina fits in, that's for sure.
Or well, we fit in with Gina.
I think he was going in with reservations at first,
but he's coming out of his shell,
that is very positive.
But it seems to me that there is an undercurrent
of politics in our tribe.
Have you ever felt someone else
just by putting your hands in front of them?
- Paschal is looking at us like...
- Wait, wait, you have to go slowly.
Now, tell me when you feel hot.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry?
Can't you feel the heat?
Paschal, you are desensitized.
You are old and desensitized.
That's right.
I am very concerned about the Paschal-Neleh union,
and that Gina will steal my job.
- Neleh.
- Yes.
Close your eyes. Close them.
Don't open them. I want you to smell.
Tell me what you smell. What do you smell?
Wait. It's very sweet.
Candy?
It is soft. Let's cut it.
For me, Gina is part of the tribe, there is no more Rotu,
we are a united tribe,
and that's how I'm going to finish this game.
- Oh, man.
- I can smell it from here.
The virgin.
I love Gina to death, and now I feel closer to her than to the others in the tribe.
than the others in the tribe.
As soon as Gabe was kicked out,
I knew there was an alliance with those 4 from Rotu.
I would have liked to see them lie to my face,
when I asked them if there was or not.
Can I ask you a question?
You, The General, Tammy and John,
don't you four have an alliance?
We have a friendship, not an alliance.
Interesting.
I knew he was lying as soon as he told me.
I just knew it.
Don't sit there telling me that you're 100% sincere
and that everything is 100% legitimate,
and then you turn around to lie to me
and stab me in the back.
Because, whether I play or not, I don't forget.
You know what I mean?
I understand what you are saying.
I don't trust Zoe.
At this point,
I trust no one but myself.
I mean, if we win tomorrow,
there's still game for us.
What's up, man?
The truth is that I was fed up with the emptiness
of the emptiness that John and the other 4 Rotu were giving us,
and wanted to get it all out in the open.
Are you telling me to my face that the four of you don't have an alliance?
- The 4 of you?
- No, how can you say we don't have it?
You'd have to be blind not to see it.
Zoe told me to my face,
not five minutes ago, John.
Maybe she doesn't think so.
John.
Hey, have I lied to you before?
Do I have "stupid" written on my forehead?
- For me, in my mind, yes.
- Of course there is an alliance.
Okay, that's what I'm saying,
now you're being honest.
I appreciate your sincerity.
But if we're going to talk about that,
we also have to talk about when we were going to kick Gabe out.
Your behavior towards me changed completely
and you were trying to find a scenario to throw me out.
Not to you in particular, but to someone from....
Look me in the eye and tell me it wasn't me.
- It wasn't you.
- Uh, uh, yeah, right.
Do I have "stupid" written on my forehead?
But you are our team.
You are here.
We have numerical superiority.
If there is a traditional merger, in the end,
3 of them and 7 of us,
they 3 will go first.
It is my unmovable word.
The only thing that scares me is that I don't trust you.
I don't trust you.
I promise I won't try to win over the other side,
or anything like that.
I promise to tell you everything straight.
I give you my word 100%,
we will not try to get the old Rotu to kick you out.
It's not going to happen, okay?
And don't try to fuck with me.
Okay. I'll take your word for it.
- Will do.
- Okay.
Same to you, man.
I think, to some extent, I may have convinced him that I am part of the team.
that I am part of the team.
I want him to trust me, but he should not.
Are you gay, man?
Hey, don't ask me that.
Don't you want to say it?
Yes, I am.
It was very passive-aggressive,
kind of spitting out the comment,
"Hey, are you gay?"
But hey, look, I'm 36 years old.
I came out of the closet a long time ago,
So I said, "Yeah, look, yeah."
I said, thank you for getting me out.
But this 36-year-old gay guy from Omaha is pulling the strings.
is the one pulling the strings.
The immunity challenge is critical for me.
If we don't win that challenge,
I will probably leave tomorrow.
Sean, V. and Tammy have to play for immunity today.
in today's immunity,
because they sat down yesterday.
I will be the fourth member.
I am not going to withdraw, I want to participate.
If we lose, and it's my last challenge,
at least I want to know that I gave it my all.
Tammy and the General and I have had a couple of conversations about who would leave next.
about who would be the next to go
if we lose immunity.
I'm just saying, I mean,
I try to stay two steps ahead.
Rob is desperate to do something.
I think we would be much better off
if Rob didn't get to the merger, period.
He's a bit dangerous,
and we have a chance to get rid of him.
My instinct is screaming at me that it would be better to lose the challenge,
and lose this voice, this dangerous person that Rob represents.
But the point is, I'm not going to lose on purpose.
- I can't go and not try.
- Just don't do anything extra, like....
help if they get left behind. I am serious.
We are talking about a million dollars at stake.
What I was trying to say to Tammy
is that there are certain battles that have to be won,
and certain battles that do not.
I hate the fact that I'm in this challenge
and you don't want to win it.
I don't know what to tell you,
it's better for him to go.
To be totally honest,
I don't know what I'm going to do when the time comes in the challenge.
I just don't know.
Go ahead, guys.
Welcome.
First things first.
Immunity is back in the air.
Today's immunity challenge is a giant maze.
Hidden in the maze,
there are 5 crossbeams that each tribe will use to make a ladder.
Each tribe will start next to the other.
You will go in opposite directions to find the first crossbeam.
The first tribe to collect the 5 crossbars
in order from 1 to 5,
build the ladder from top to bottom,
and one person climbs up with the flag, wins immunity.
To make it more interesting,
you will be tied up during the process.
At stake is the vote.
Win today, guarantee yourself a one in 10 chance of being
of being the sole survivor.
Lose, and your tribe will go to Tribal Council,
where another person will be eliminated.
Rotu, as you have 3 extra, you seat 3.
Choose your 4.
Let's tie you up.
Kathy leads Maraamuu,
Rob leads Rotu.
John, General, Zoe, you are out.
Survivors ready!
Go!
Left, left, left, left, left.
More?
Remember that.
Ready, left.
We go to the left.
On the left.
Left, left, left.
Okay, turn around.
Okay.
Come on, we have to go faster.
Right, we go right.
There is something there.
Okay, what is this?
Yellow.
Yellow, but what number?
Two.
Two points.
Yes!
Quickly, quickly.
Hurry up, guys.
Come on, we have to go faster.
Okay. Number 4.
There are a lot of blues there.
Inside, inside.
Rotu gets a head start.
I want to get to the other side, guys.
Okay, we are behind.
I know, I just want to tell you what I do.
There, go to the left.
Okay.
Okay, we need three.
Way to go, Rob, way to go!
Large circular labyrinth,
Way to go, Rotu.
You're doing great.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Hurry, hurry.
Okay, we have one.
Release me.
The three is going to be there.
Wait a minute, I have to get my bearings.
To get back to the center,
I think we have to go around this way.
Rotu has 3.
Maraamu, finally in the race.
Okay, guys, help me get back.
Hurry up!
Okay.
Let's go, let's go.
3 is this way.
Rotu has 3, Maraamu 2!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Left, right, left, right, left, right.
Kathy, on the other side.
What?
Go back the other way, honey.
That was 4, not 3.
Why can't we go around this thing?
Let's go. We have to get to the outer circle.
We can't, is there no way out?
Go this way, go to the right.
- This way, Kathy, this way.
- That's not it.
We've been there a hundred times.
No, we have to go through there.
See, over there?
You have to move, you have to move.
Rotu has 4, Maraamu 2!
Come on, this is the last one.
Let's go, let's go.
Guys, we have to go faster.
Nothing.
Step lightly, baby.
Light step.
Let's go.
Rotu wins!
Guys, stop.
- The first victory.
- Here we are!
Maraamu, I am sorry to tell you that tomorrow is Tribal Council,
one of the 4 will go home.
- How was your day?
- Fine.
I have taken troca and cowrie.
Really?
A lot?
4 trocas and I think 5...
Good job.
When we got back there was no fire,
and I was feeling pretty bad.
I did not do well as a leader in the labyrinth,
and when I returned I drowned the fire.
You have to remove the sand.
I fired it up this morning without taking out the sand.
Gina and I often argue about throwing sand on the fire.
I always put sand in Rotu,
and it worked great.
Maybe the sand was different there.
We are low on firewood, so we only...
I piled it up, made a bed of embers and covered it.
The sand suffocates the game when it touches it.
What if we pile up a lot of burning embers?
These are not hot.
Some were hot
when I dug them up.
Well, not anymore.
He said that in Rotu they threw sand into the fire
so that the embers would be hot,
and I know that every time I go camping, we throw sand on the fire
we throw sand on the fire to put it out.
As much as there was burning,
it was not enough.
I don't think it's going to turn on.
I was hoping that we would go to Tribal Council
and vote tonight and then have a conversation.
But I went to talk to Gina about it,
and she didn't think we should talk about it.
So I'm not going to bring it up.
They do not like the subject.
No, they don't like it.
I don't think they have enough nerve to talk about it.
to talk about it.
I do not agree at all,
I think we should embrace it, man,
get it out in the open and enjoy the rest of the day.
- The fire is out.
- Is it out?
No fire.
Nothing? Are you sure?
We know you have to leave,
and it is a difficult decision.
I don't think they're going to vote for me
just because I wasn't with them at the beginning.
I may be wrong, but I don't feel that way.
I just don't like his idea of sand.
This is how fires are put out.
That's what I thought, too.
If I do personal strategy,
I would have to vote for Kathy,
because I know automatically that Neleh and Paschal
are not going to vote for each other.
Have you eaten them raw before?
You need lemon.
They are hard as rocks.
I'm not going to start tonight.
To tell you the truth, I haven't decided what I'm going to do.
I've been going back and forth all day.
I know for sure I'm not going to vote for Paschal,
but between Kathy and Gina, I find it very difficult.
Look, if you think about it,
we went to sleep many nights without eating anything.
Tonight we go to Tribal Council
and everyone is going to stand up and vote,
and it will be a secret until that very moment.
All right, let's get down to business.
A lot has happened.
This small tribe of 4,
the real anti-favorites,
proved to be very strong.
Paschal, what kind of tribe is this?
What things have changed since you were last here?
If you would have told me when I left Rotu
that we were going to duplicate what we had there,
I would have said no way.
We have not only doubled it, we have gone even further.
Really.
So let's talk about loyalties.
- Kathy, where does your loyalty fall now?
- I think the spirit of Rotu
still lurks on the other beach.
But it has diminished, and we have formed something that is truly united.
I think the two tribes have dissipated,
and we are creating something new.
If there was a merger tonight,
would the four of you still be together,
or would that be a hey, Gina, we had a good time,
see if we can infiltrate Rotu's force of numbers?
No, the 4 of us would continue together, as a block.
Of course, all 4.
Neleh.
Of course.
What do you think, Gina?
Are you still the black sheep,
or are you now really part of a tribe of 4?
We are a tribe, of course.
I would even call it a family.
Tonight we do not want to expel anyone.
Kathy, let's talk about yesterday's immunity challenge.
You were dragging these people along
as if they were schoolchildren who don't want to get up.
Did you ever think, wow,
I hope we're still a tribe,
and I hope they don't intend to make me the scapegoat?
I went with my head down because I felt I had failed the tribe in the challenge.
But on the other hand, there is such a feeling of family among the 4 of us,
that I felt better when we came out of the labyrinth.
and returned to camp.
So, if you are such a close-knit family,
how are you going to vote tonight?
How do you make that decision?
Neleh?
Every ten minutes I come up with someone new.
I don't even know how many times it has crossed my mind,
because I don't want anyone to leave.
Have you already made a decision?
Honestly, no.
Okay.
It is time to vote.
Paschal, you are the first.
I am going to recount the votes.
As soon as I read the votes, the decision is final.
The person eliminated will have to leave the Tribal Council area immediately.
the Tribal Council area immediately.
I read the votes.
Gina.
Kathy.
2 votes Gina, 1 vote Kathy.
Decisive vote:
Gina.
You have to bring me the torch.
I love you.
Gina, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, you guys have insisted on using the word "family" tonight,
instead of tribe.
Sometimes families have to make difficult decisions.
I'm sure this has been one of the worst.
You can go back to camp.
See you tomorrow.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
In the next episode of Survivor:
The two tribes merge.
I am very happy to see you.
Father in heaven,
we are very grateful for the unions among us.
Amen.
But... can they all live happily under the same roof?
Tell the truth for once, right?
Zoe is lying to me.
They are all lying to me.
In this game no one knows who is telling the truth.
Don't lie to my face.
You asked for it, man.
Miss Kathy, Paschal and Neleh, you guys are great.
I love you all.
I understand tonight's vote.
The remaining members of the tribe... I hope you play well,
with cleanliness, and with strength.
and it has been a wonderful, wonderful few days.
Nothing can ever replace this experience.