>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor : Rob and Kathy
prepared for the merge and made
a pact to protect each other.
>> I am really serious.
Don't stab me.
>> I swear to God I will never
vote you off.
>> PROBST: The next day Maraamu
had to break camp and set sail
for Rotu where the two tribes
merge.
>> One, two, three, Soliantu.
>> PROBST: But unity was short-
lived.
In an attempt to undermine the
original Rotu alliance of four,
Rob confronted Zoe.
>> Tell the truth for once, will
ya?
>> They're all lying to me.
I need the immunity because I'm
getting the ax.
>> PROBST: At the challenge,
Kathy won a crucial immunity.
Back at camp, tensions flared,
bringing chaos to Soliantu.
>> Everybody was like, we a
team, we a team.
Soon as these three come over...
>> All right, all right.
Well, everything's coming out
tonight.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Rob was voted off.
Rob, the tribe has spoken.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I know it's a somber mood
because we had to vote somebody
out, but you guys, we're all on
the jury.
That's a huge accomplishment.
You guys should all feel really
good.
>> I feel great.
>> I feel wonderful.
>> I feel wonderful, too.
>> Wonderful, wonderful.
>> Before Tribal Council, I
pulled Rob aside and I told him
that I was going to be voting
for him, and he was okay about
it.
But I wanted him to hear it from
me and I didn't want him to
think that I was trying to do
anything behind his back,
especially being a previous
Maraamu and having an agreement
with him at one time.
>> Have the last couple of
nights been kind of cold for you
guys?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> Like colder than usual, huh?
>> After the Tribal Council,
with Rob being gone, the mood
around here is so totally
different.
It's so much more relaxed and
peaceful, you know.
There isn't a threat that some
wise-ass remark's going to be
made and set off a whole new
fight going on for no good
reason.
>> Who farted?
>> I did.
>> It stinks.
>> Excuse me.
That was the first fart that
actually had substance.
>> This diet has played havoc, I
guess, with Sean's system,
because he does have a little
bit of a flatulent problem, but
I sleep down the other end of
the tent and I'm usually upwind,
so I've been a little bit
fortunate.
>> I'm sorry, y'all.
I thought it was enough time to
air it out over here, but...
>> Sean is definitely... you
know, he'll probably the next
one voted off.
Everybody's talking about Sean
being a problem.
He just doesn't work hard.
He complains.
He farts a lot.
>> What was that?
>> I'm just messing everybody
up.
>> Dude.
>> Sean...
>> I'm sorry.
>> You're sleeping somewhere
else.
>> I'm playing the game exactly
how I came in playing, which is
if you're true to yourself,
that's the true game of life.
The only thing that's changing
is my attitude.
(breaks wind)
Oh, see how happy I am?
I can pass gas and feel free as
a bird.
>> Sean.
>> Wasn't me.
I cleaned mine.
Some nasty ass over here...
>> Good night, everybody.
>> Good night.
>> I got up before daybreak.
I was out by the fire.
I couldn't sleep, so I got out
and I was sitting by the fire
thinking of my wife and my
daughters.
>> We got up this morning, and
there was... we had a real windy
night and a real windy morning,
and as you can see, two trees
came right down on camp.
We're very lucky that they fell
this way instead of falling on
our... falling on our tent.
>> Yeah, a couple more feet and
that could have been on our
tent.
>> Don't say that.
But it wasn't.
Praise God.
>> We have to go over what
happened yesterday.
I was just confused about the
fact that if there was an
original alliance to vote me off
first when I came here.
I just wanted to know about it.
>> Definitely not, Kathy.
>> Okay.
>> But was there one formed just
to get Rob in a different
position?
>> That was my intention, and
that's what I tried to express
yesterday.
There was never any intention of
voting you off in no way in
hell.
We wanted to get Rotu back
together as a team.
>> Zoe just lied to me
point-blank about the fact that
the tribe had definitely scoped
me out for the first vote off
when we merged.
I think Zoe's been lying from
the beginning.
I think she's been playing both
sides, and I just can't take
that.
Whoever wins wins, but I don't
want to be the pawn, you know?
>> Right.
>> So I'm going to fight tooth
and nail to find out what's
going on.
But not to the point where I
upset my friendships.
I don't want to upset
friendships with people.
>> I don't either.
>> I was going to push her
further on it, but I just
decided for good negotiations,
not to get voted off.
I wanted her to feel a little
guilty.
I think I did that.
>> But I'm just happy that we
got through this, and then when
Sean's voted off...
>> One day at a time.
>> ...then we'll deal with what
we're doing with each other, all
right?
>> Good.
>> Okay, good.
Thanks, sweetie.
♪ ♪
>> I don't know why, but I get
empowered by these waterfalls.
It's the freshwater and it's
just... it's invigorating.
So I wanted to be up there and
just feel that pressure point on
my back and kind of wake up and
start a new day in a better
direction.
>> There, you got it.
>> 5.8.
>> Nobody has ever complained
about going to the waterfall
because that's one place where
we go, jump in the water, it's
nice and cold.
It cools us off and totally
refreshes us.
For me, it rejuvenates
everything inside of me, and I'm
ready to go again after I get
out of there.
>> Oh, my God, look, you guys.
What is it?
They're, like, flags or
something.
>> And when we got up the
waterfall and we were on our way
back, we checked the tree mail
and sure enough, we had tree
mail.
>> Oh, my God, they're
umbrellas.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> These are kites.
>> This is like a picnic thing,
I think.
>> Wow.
Let's bring back the whole
basket, so everybody can see it.
That is cool.
>> You guys, check this out.
So it says here: "You may be
feeling grounded.
Now how high can you go?
Find the wind under your wings
to see wonders down below.
Here's some items to build a
kite, though you're not
restricted to just these.
Make yours fly the highest first
and you'll explore these exotic
seas."
Taking you out in a boat and
you're going to eat.
It was a pretty cool tree mail.
It was a really good twist of
trying to make kites and then we
have to fly them and then we get
a reward.
>> (yelling)
Too much wind.
>> I got a kite and a new outfit
out of this challenge.
>> I think the next facet of
this game is to eliminate the
non-Rotu people.
I think Sean will go first, but
I don't think we're going to
start voting off power.
I want to, believe me.
I would love to vote off John or
Tammy, but I don't know if I can
really get Paschal to listen.
He likes to make his own
decisions about honesty and
trustworthiness.
>> See, I asked Zoe that.
I just point-blank asked her:
"Did you guys ever consider
voting me off?"
And she said no.
>> Well, that's true.
They didn't.
You're getting all this negative
stuff.
>> You know, if I'm used as a
pawn for them to win and I'm on
the jury and I have to vote for
them and they took me and...
>> We'll find out.
>> Yeah, but they're going to
use us to get to the top.
>> So?
>> All right.
I need to have Paschal and Neleh
experience some of this turmoil.
A couple more pieces of turmoil
and they see how people act,
then they might commit to
understanding that the powerful
people need to go.
>> Oh, my kite is going to be a
miserable failure.
>> Oh, stop it.
>> I'm serious.
>> Ah, go fly a kite.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Welcome, guys.
Today's challenge is very
simple.
The first person to get their
kite 300 feet in the air wins.
You'll know you're at 300 feet
because at the end of your spool
you'll see a purple ribbon.
Once that clears your spool, you
win.
Now, to the reward, and I hope
this brings a smile to your
face.
To start, a delicious Snickers
bar.
Ain't no regular Snickers
either.
It's the big one.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Freshly chilled
on ice...
All right, start down here.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: Dig in.
>> Oh, my God.
This is so good.
>> PROBST: Dig in, John.
The winner of the reward gets
the king-size Snickers, and
you're going to eat it en route
to a deep sea dive in one of the
most spectacular places on
Earth.
A good chance to see manta rays,
eels, hammerhead sharks.
You go out with somebody
experienced.
They'll teach you everything you
need to know.
Have a great time.
All right, pick your spool.
Tie it up to your kite.
Spread out along the beach.
Wait for my go.
Here we go, guys.
Survivors ready?
Go!
That-a-way, Kathy.
Off to a good start.
♪ ♪
That-a-way, Zoe.
All right, Neleh, you're
airborne.
♪ ♪
Hang in there, Tammy.
>> Fly!
This thing just does not want to
fly.
>> PROBST: Sean, you're getting
nowhere fast, buddy.
Paschal, what are you doing?
Come on, John, run.
Run!
>> Good job, girlfriend.
That's tough.
>> PROBST: That-a-way, Zoe.
Keep it going.
You're up.
You're down.
♪ ♪
There you go, Neleh.
Oh, you're back on the ground.
♪ ♪
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
Whoa!
>> PROBST: You're on a hot
streak.
Do you dive?
>> Yeah.
>> Do you?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> PROBST: You're going to have
a great time.
>> Oh, I know.
>> Look at my kite.
It looks like the Little Rascals
built it.
>> PROBST: Guys, let's bring it
in.
You're going down looking for
sharks.
You're looking for eels.
You're looking for manta rays.
You're going to have a nice cool
Snickers.
You guys can head back to camp
that way.
♪ ♪
>> The seas out in the South
Pacific are crazy.
They're so squirrelly.
They're going one way, another
way.
If you hit one of those large
swells, the zodiac just comes
slamming down.
It was really fun.
I was definitely apprehensive.
>> The nice thing about scuba
diving that you've got to
remember is just to relax.
So as soon as you relax,
everything becomes really easy.
>> Right.
>> Just go through the hand
sequence.
>> Okay.
>> You're okay.
>> Not good.
>> I've got one of my own.
>> Yeah?
>> When I'm really scared,
I go...
They had everything ready
to go, you know?
Wetsuit, tanks, they were
informing me.
I felt very confident.
And by the time I was all suited
up and I was about ready to do
that back-flip off the boat, I
just said, "Just keep going,
Kath."
Ready.
>> Ready?
>> Dive.
>> The feeling when you first go
underwater, it's like going from
day to night, only it's going
from air to a whole 'nother
world under there.
You really truly feel like a
fish out of water, you know.
This isn't our abode.
There isn't where we're supposed
to be, and I feel that I'm
infiltrating something--
that we're not supposed to be
down there, but it's gorgeous.
There were some rays kicking
around.
And the amount of fish is equal
to being in a massive aquarium.
It was a vacation down there,
getting away from the tribe and
the island and everything.
I just feel like I'm so far away
from everything down there.
No stress.
>> The bottom line is every
single Tribal Council, we go in
with the first we know we're
voting off and we're going with
a backup person.
>> Okay, it sounds good.
>> Right now, Paschal, Neleh,
myself, Big Rob, John and Zoe,
we've all decided to vote the
same for the next three votes.
Sean is the one.
>> I'm trying to leave here
playing the game.
I get frustrated because I feel
like nobody's playing the game.
I know I'm definitely next.
I didn't come out for no
vacation.
I came out to bring home the
bacon.
I'm not...
All I can do is go out trying.
I'm telling you the truth.
I'm going to talk to Kathy and
I'm going to talk to Neleh.
>> Sean, I think, probably is
feeling very vulnerable right
now and is trying to stir the
pot a little bit, to cause some
possible doubts about what's
going to happen tomorrow night
in the event he doesn't win
immunity or whether or not he's
got the votes to keep him on.
So it's fascinating to watch
all this take place.
>> Let's pray for a moment.
Father God, in the name of
Jesus, another grateful morning
to be in your presence.
>> God, that was hysterical.
I feel like a dead fish.
Hey, how are you?
>> Tell me about it.
>> It was great.
It was beautiful.
It was exciting.
And we got a Snickers bar, so
I'm excited.
We're going to have some
chocolate.
The real motivational force for
bringing the Snickers bar back
was for peace of mind.
So if they had any beef that I
won a challenge again, then I
thought the Snicker bar would
just kind of entice good
feelings from the tribe.
It could also backfire, like I'm
trying to bribe them.
Oh, my God.
I am now going to be eating
Snicker bars.
We all would have had a hard
time bringing it back, so that
was very, very generous of you.
Thank you.
>> I like having you guys happy.
There's too much tension on the
beach.
>> No.
That was great.
Thanks.
>> It was a beautiful gesture on
Kathy's part, you know, an
eighth of a Snicker isn't going
to change my vote, but I do
appreciate the gesture and it
was a very sweet thing for her
to do.
>> There's a bond here.
>> Yep, there definitely is.
>> It may be a different kind of
bond, but there's a bond.
>> Right.
>> Everybody's, like, we're all
family and I'm like, you know,
everything ain't hunky-dory over
here.
Things are going on.
People are not to be trusted.
But while you're still in the
game, you've got to kind of be
vague, but still put it out.
Maybe Kathy.
If I can maybe get Kathy,
then maybe she can get Pappy and
Neleh.
At this point, all gloves is
off.
It's like, let's go for the
gusto.
This is a million bucks.
We have one in nine.
We'll never have these odds in
our favor.
This isn't just a game.
We're now going to head into
crunch time.
We have a chance to win the
million.
>> The only thing I can say is I
totally agree with you.
I think Tammy and John are
playing the game and they're
playing it so hard, it's
obnoxious.
>> If you're in agreement, you
me and V are on the same
wavelength.
>> Yeah, we are, but we just
need to get Paschal and Neleh
and you know what?
I think we can do it.
I think this alliance stuff is
what's killing us here.
>> You just know there's going
to be alliances, you know, no
matter what, so...
>> Really?
>> Yeah, no matter what.
And no matter... the bigger
stink you make about things, the
more vulnerable you are, so...
>> I know.
>> Being voted out fifth totally
is fine.
She feels if you make too many
waves, she said, "Kathy, if you
talk any more about that, you're
going to get voted off."
So now, Paschal's sort of the
pivotal vote.
I don't want to be a pawn to
help Tammy and John go to the
top.
I want it to be even.
>> I'm not aligning myself with
Sean and V.
>> You know what, Paschal?
>> No, you know what?
Here's the deal.
>> I want it to be fair.
>> Okay, here's the deal.
>> It should be fair.
>> Well, this game's not fair.
>> If I could have formed the
alliance with Sean and V and
Paschal and Neleh and myself,
I would have had a huge shot at
it, but that's not going to
happen.
Paschal wants Sean off, and so
does everybody else.
>> I'm feeling vulnerable
because of the warpath that
Sean went on, and so what I'm
worried about are there may be
people that may believe some of
the trash he was talking
and decide to vote against me.
>> Somebody who really sucked,
somebody who did nothing beat
me, that would just suck.
>> Well, that's exactly what I
told Neleh.
I said, "It is so important to
me that somebody like Sean
doesn't make it to the finals."
I said, "John deserves it.
Sean would be an embarrassment."
>> John picked up on something
that Sean may be under the
belief that he has Kathy and V
and me and Neleh with him, which
is incorrect.
And I just wanted to tell John
and I told him, I said, "You've
got my word that's not true."
When I give you my order... when
I give you my word, my word is
the most important thing to me
at my age."
I don't have much, but I got
that.
>> Neleh and Paschal, I think,
are really supporting my success
in this game and are really
rooting for me.
And knowing that you can rely
upon those two people, I mean,
it's like two free passes.
It's an amazing experience.
I mean it's actually kind of
mind-blowing.
>> Who didn't get one?
>> Is it good?
>> You didn't get any?
>> Thanks, buddy.
>> Thank you.
>> Mostly coconut with just a
little bit of taro in it.
>> I can pick the little taro
out.
>> The mood in the camp right
now seems to be, you know, we're
all on the jury and good luck to
everybody, but I do know "good
luck to everybody" really means
"good luck to Sean."
You know, every man for himself
is really Sean is for himself
swimming upstream.
>> See if my check came today,
please.
>> Pretty simple.
>> Okay.
"You've had time to learn this
place.
I hope you've prepared well.
If you've done your homework,
soon we all will tell.
Use your information wisely.
You can choose who you'll cut
down.
Hope you've played nicely.
It will help you stick around."
>> I just think it's going to
be, like, a process of
elimination maybe.
>> I don't trust any one of
these people in this game.
I'm trying to win immunity for
me.
I'm not giving it up if I win,
and if I lose, I'm going to
salute them and tell them, "Good
luck," because pretty much
that's how they wanted it.
I'm on my own.
Why would I want to trust any
one of them now at this stage
of the game?
>> PROBST: First things first.
Kathy, the immunity necklace
back up for grabs.
Okay.
For today's immunity challenge,
I'm going to ask you a series of
questions relating to life and
survival on the Marquesas
Islands.
Each of you has a station with
three bundles of coconuts
strung up to the top of a
coconut tree.
Every time you get an answer
correctly, you're going to take
the prong and chop down one pile
of coconuts of somebody else's.
You win immunity by knocking
everybody else out.
So when all three of your
coconut bundles have been
chopped down, you're out of the
game.
The last person left with
coconuts wins immunity.
Now, if more than one of you has
a correct answer, you'll each
get a turn at chopping down
coconuts in an order chosen at
random.
Get up your blocks and let's do
it.
All right, here we go.
First question: True or false:
in a prolonged survival
situation, drinking large
quantities of coconut milk will
help combat dehydration?
The correct answer is false.
It has a laxative effect.
General, step forward.
Tammy, step forward.
Sean, step forward.
Sean, you're first.
Tammy, you're second.
General, you go third.
>> Surprise, surprise.
Shock of all shocks.
>> Good form, man.
Good form.
>> PROBST: The game is on, huh,
Sean?
>> It's always been.
>> All right, Tammy.
>> PROBST: All right, Tammy.
>> Oh, I see what's going on.
>> PROBST: General.
Let's get this game going.
You're a marked man, Sean.
>> That's all right.
>> PROBST: Next question.
Cannibalism was common in the
Marquesas for which of the
following reasons:
A: as a means of purging the
sins of a tribe?
B: as a source of protein due to
the scarcity of meat?
C: a form of tribal sacrifice?
Or D: to seize the power of the
person being eaten?
The correct answer is D.
They wanted to seize the power.
John, V, Zoe, Sean and Neleh,
all got it right.
>> Kathy, I love you.
You're on a roll, girl.
No hurt feelings, though.
>> Nice job, baby.
>> Stay away from that green.
>> Oh, that was a tough one for
him.
Payback's a bitch.
Good man.
>> Sean?
>> I got that, baby, right here.
>> PROBST: All right, Sean,
you're the first casualty.
You can take your box, have a
seat right over here in the
viewing area.
Neleh.
>> Go, Sweet Pea.
>> PROBST: Vecepia takes a first
hit.
>> Sweet Pea, whoa, you'll be
cracking some nuts.
>> Oh, there's a conspiracy
going on, y'all.
>> Three strikes and you're....
>> I'm calling Johnny Cochran,
if somebody hits V's.
>> PROBST: True or false: Within
a survival situation at sea
without freshwater, you should
refrain from eating?
True or false?
The answer is true.
John, General, Paschal, Zoe,
Tammy.
>> Where's Johnny Cochran?
I want him on the phone right
now.
>> PROBST: Vecepia, you join
Sean in the waiting area.
Kathy takes her second hit.
>> You look tired, Kathy.
>> Ow!
>> PROBST: Kathy's out of the
game, joins Sean and V.
Paschal takes his first hit.
>> Whoa!
>> A little to the right, John.
>> Sorry, Neleh.
>> PROBST: Neleh's got one hit.
>> Ow.
>> PROBST: With authority.
>> Yeah!
>> I swear we could take them
out, I swear we could.
>> I don't know if we had
Paschal and Neleh for sure,
though.
>> What, dear?
>> I said that was ugly of you.
>> PROBST: John, General just
took you out, but you still get
a shot.
>> This is the order how it's
going to go.
That's my boy.
>> You guys are cooking tonight.
>> PROBST: Paschal, you're out.
John, you're also out.
You can join the other three.
All right, Neleh.
General has all three of his
bundles of coconuts left.
Zoe and Neleh and Tammy, you
each have two left now.
Next question: In the Marquesas
Islands, what is a horse?
A: a rearing flower.
B: a vermilion sea creature
found in lagoons.
C: a horse like any other found
all over the world.
Or D: a traditional podium for
tiki statues.
Spanish explorers introduced
horses to the Marquesas, so a
horse is just a horse.
Everybody but Zoe step forward.
>> Everybody's got to have two,
also, right?
>> Ow!
Oh, nice.
>> One last person in the game
evens the odds.
>> Oh, good.
I needed a rest.
I'll remember.
Don't worry.
>> PROBST: Payback's tough.
>> Heads up, General.
>> You want me to leave it out
for you?
>> Ooh.
>> Why wouldn't she have given
Neleh another chance?
>> You whacked me.
Turnaround is fair play.
>> PROBST: Take your box and
join the group.
>> Hey, it's green.
Money.
Money color, baby.
>> PROBST: It's down to you two.
You both get it right,
we'll move on.
Somebody misses, it's over.
True or false: The sea cucumber
can actually be deadly to human
beings?
It can cause burns, but it is
not deadly.
Tammy's right.
Chop down his last coconut.
I'll have immunity when you get
back.
>> Oh, doesn't that look
beautiful?
>> PROBST: Nicely done.
Tammy's safe from the vote.
Somebody else is going home.
See you at Tribal Council in a
few hours.
You guys can head back to camp.
Nice job.
So long.
>> You know how people always
say everything is not perfect.
When you get back from a
challenge, you find out just how
everything is not always
perfect.
>> Took care of business right
off the bat, man.
Thank you, baby.
>> At the challenge, there was
quite a bit of cockiness with
Tammy, Zoe, Big Rob and John.
>> I almost was going to do you
because I hated to get Paschal
at another time.
>> It didn't seem to bother you
that much.
>> Today in the trivia game,
Sean went out first, then V,
then Kathy.
I had some satisfaction that I
was the one that cut Sean's last
rope.
So hopefully that will be an
omen tonight.
>> Everybody saw for their own
eyes at the challenge how
arrogant the four was, and I
think it rubs people the wrong
way.
>> They just didn't play it
smart in that game.
>> They didn't.
>> Yeah, they were never going
to give us any consideration.
>> No way.
>> None.
>> I think the way that immunity
came down, the coconut chopping
and all, I think it signaled to
us that there was a pecking
order, and we were included in
it, even though we had been told
that that wasn't true.
>> When we saw the coconuts,
they hacked down John's, you
know, these just in the order
that they were going to
eliminate us.
I've been nothing but honest to
everybody.
I'm following my heart today.
I would be lying to my heart and
to myself if I went up there and
voted for Sean tonight.
This is really how I feel,
Paschal.
If me and you are going to get
anywhere towards the end, we
have to do this.
We would be fools not to.
I'm not going to go out with
those six.
We've worked too hard.
We've been here for too long,
worked too hard, and I'm not
going to go out like that.
I just had this feeling, you
know, especially after today's
immunity challenge.
I saw them hack down Paschal's
coconuts so fast, and inside I'm
just like, there's got to be
something changed here.
>> I don't know how to play this
game.
I have no clue how to play it.
I don't want to know how to play
it.
I tend to lay back and watch the
lay of the land and then when I
think I've got the lay of the
land figured out, I begin doing
something.
This is exactly how I am in the
courtroom, in life.
The only thing I can say is I
think I'm a fair and consistent
judge.
I think I'm a fair and
consistent player.
>> I'm going to pack all my
stuff, and when I go to Tribal,
I'm fully prepared to be voted
out.
If it's going to be that they
vote me out ninth, I don't like
going out like a wimp because
I'd rather go out with my head
held high knowing that I tried,
than staying around dealing with
the tribal people saying, well,
at least five, six or seven is
not bad.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Welcome, guys.
>> Jeff.
>> Hi, Jeff.
>> PROBST: V, about today's
challenge.
Do you think there was anything
to the first three who got
knocked out of this game?
Sean was clearly marked.
You were next and Kathy.
Boom, boom, boom.
Is that just the way this game
goes, or did you reflect upon
that and think, "Hmm?"
>> Jeff, I definitely reflected
upon that because it seemed to
me to be a little bit of
gloating as people were staying
in the game and going on,
and it was apparent to several
of us, and at that point, alarms
started going off in all of our
heads.
>> PROBST: John, tell me about
the kiss.
You gave a Godfather kiss to
Sean as you went to do his third
one.
Sean received it, good-naturedly
and put it on his ass.
What was going on there?
>> Basically with me being the
mouthpiece and you're dead-on,
that's exactly what I was doing,
you know, just taunting.
We have a friendship with each
other where we understand that
we're playing the game, and that
nothing is meant seriously.
We have no hard feelings toward
each other at all.
>> PROBST: Paschal, for you,
what's the objective of this
game?
You've been out here now 24
days.
>> Well, from my point of view,
the objective when I came in
here was to be as honest as I
could be, given the framework of
the game.
And I'm one of the people that
really didn't start playing the
game until very late.
I think I started maybe playing
today, as a matter of fact.
>> PROBST: How about for you,
John?
>> I came into the game wanting
to be, you know, Mr. Integrity,
Mr. Honesty.
And then you start building
alliances and you start doing
things, and then there is doubt
about what other people are
saying or doing.
I don't think I, like, flat out
lied.
I think I've adapted to the half
truths and all that, and I've
done my share of them, you know,
and I wish I hadn't, but at this
point, it just seems to be part
of the game.
>> PROBST: Sean, if you get
voted out tonight, are you proud
of how you've played?
>> I'm proud 100%.
I haven't lied to one person in
this game.
The people I kept my word to,
I've kept my word to up to this
point.
For me, integrity is definitely
important.
Stand for something or you'll
fall for anything.
So stand up for what you
believe, even if it means
getting kicked out.
>> PROBST: Okay, immunity.
Tammy, you're wearing it.
You own it.
You can keep it.
You can certainly give it away.
What are you going to do with
it?
>> When I went into the immunity
challenge today, I didn't give a
(bleep) whether I won or lost
because I wasn't worried about
my position in the tribe.
But I hold this thing in high
respect now, and I realize how
valuable it is.
>> PROBST: So you're keeping it.
Okay, you guys are about to get
ready to vote out the first
person that will be a member of
the jury.
From here on out, you're going
to vote people out of this game
and then turn around and ask
them to come back and vote for
you to give you $1 million.
Very, very tough game to play.
It is time to vote.
Paschal, you're first.
>> You told me today you can't
wait for a shower, a meal and a
good bed.
We'll be hanging at NYC
eating good soon.
Later, bro.
>> You've been better the last
few days, but I still don't feel
like you pull your weight around
the camp.
>> Checkmate, brother.
You thought you had me.
Any time you go to Vegas, bet on
black.
We're definitely going to have
chicken and waffles when this
whole thing is done.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sean.
Sean.
Two votes Sean.
John.
It's two votes Sean;
two votes John.
Three votes John.
We're tied: three votes John,
three votes Sean.
That's four votes John.
The eighth person voted out,
the first member of our jury:
John.
No need to read the last vote.
John, the tribe has spoken.
>> Okeydoke.
>> PROBST: It's time for you to
go.
Good night.
Just when you think you have
this game figured out, whoops,
surprise.
This game is up for grabs.
You guys can head back to camp.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
John's departure marks a new era
at Soliantu.
>> It's a new day we're starting
here!
>> PROBST: Friends become bitter
enemies.
>> From the get-go I didn't like
you.
>> I have changed my opinion of
Zoe.
Zoe's a bitch.
>> PROBST: And two lucky
survivors get away from it all.
Now for the reward:
an authentic Marquesan feast.
>> Well, well, well.
So I'm the first member of the
jury.
I'm going to go eat really good
food.
My abs are incredible.
I wish I could have done a
little bit better.
You won't be able to retire,
Mom.
I'm sorry.
But, um, but I made the game and
I made the jury and I just...
I did really well and I'm very
proud of myself.