>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: John made an alliance
with the other three original
Rotu members and took control of
the tribe.
>> Everyone knows I'm the
leader.
Everyone knows it's my plan.
>> PROBST: But Rob and Sean were
left out of the alliance and
have their own plans for John.
>> If I have any opportunity at
all to get rid of John, I will.
>> PROBST: Rob and John decided
to make a pitch and join John's
alliance.
>> I'm giving you my word, 100%.
>> PROBST: They cut a deal.
In case of a merge they'll vote
together to eliminate Maraamu
first.
>> I want them to trust me, but
he shouldn't.
>> PROBST: Go!
Rob then led Rotu to victory in
the immunity challenge,
>> Rotu wins!
>> PROBST ...sending Maraamu to
Tribal Council, where they voted
Gina out of the tribe.
The tribe has spoken.
Ten survivors remain.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> It's a skull of a man!
>> Oh, that's definitely a
skull.
>> What is that?
Is that the eyeball socket?
>> Yeah.
That's the eye socket.
>> Oh!
>> This is unbelievable.
>> It really is.
>> It's hard to believe how many
centuries we're looking at right
here.
>> Look, that's his ribcage.
Do we agree that's a paepae?
>> It is a paepae because these
rocks are too evenly formed.
A paepae is a Marquesan
monument.
That's where they had their
ceremonies and where they even
performed cannibalism.
>> They just buried them in the
side of a wall?
>> Look at how this skull is
fractured.
>> Yeah, that's what I was
talking about.
>> It's obvious it had some
blunt trauma to the head.
A fracture all the way across
here.
>> I think it was an emotional
day.
Last night, it was tough.
Tough vote.
I was happy at one point that
the vote went my way, but when I
saw Gina leave, I felt really
bad.
>> Go over here, back under...
>> Paschal and Neleh, I don't
think I can break up that
situation.
They have a really great bond.
Because we're at three right
now, I have to work it.
It'll be tough.
I think if we do get to another
vote, they'll vote me off.
>> You're thinking of catching a
piglet.
I'm thinking of catching a pig.
I mean there are a bunch of pigs
running around.
There's one right there.
>> This tribe is a bunch of
morons.
I've just about had it with this
tribe.
>> Hello.
>> How are you?
Good morning.
>> Doing great.
>> Vecepia is just so fake to
me.
The way people are acting, it
drives me crazy.
Maybe that's their game.
Everybody is going to be happy
to each other, but I hate it.
I think at the other camp I
always had an ace in the hole,
and over here I don't.
>> The only thing is we don't
know if they're keeping their
word.
Say, like, they get rid of Kathy
like they said the first time,
but then say just as a
precaution they might get rid of
one of us.
Just so we can't do an alliance.
I've been stuck in a roadblock
situation for the past ten days,
and I haven't been able to get
around it.
And it's like I've tried going
up one side of the mountain and
I've tried going up the other
side, and maybe it's time to try
to just dig a hole right through
it.
>> Mail call.
Okay, ladies!
>> No, you.
>> Yeah, go right ahead.
Oh, it's a long one.
>> It's a long one.
"You'll be left in stitches if
you sew up this reward.
Give this map to one survivor.
Defeat can you not afford.
Choose your one wisely with
long sleeves and long pants.
Don't send the wrong tribe
mate.
This may be your last chance."
One of us has to leave.
>> There's a map here.
We've got five minutes to pick
one person, get them outfitted
in long-sleeved pants, tennis
shoes, and have them start
following this map.
Okay, who do we want to send?
>> I'll volunteer.
I'll go do it.
>> Is there anybody else that
wants to go do this one?
>> Okay, that's fine.
>> I've got five minutes?
>> Less than that now.
Put on long pants.
>> I'm going to do it for us.
Rotu, come on.
>> All right, man, Rotu, Rotu.
>> I got my pack.
I'll take some mango.
Thank you.
Give me the map.
>> Be careful!
>> I will.
>> Where's the knife?
Give me a knife.
>> You going to want socks also?
>> Might as well, right?
>> We're all counting on you,
babe.
Put some coconut in your pocket.
Come on, boy.
>> Now it's in God's hands.
>> Yeah, I volunteered because
I thought there may be a change
and something might be getting
shaken up.
But that's how I've been playing
this game.
I've been taking chances.
>> PROBST: Hey, guys.
Hey.
>> PROBST: How you doing, man?
Kathy, how are you?
>> Good to see you.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Kamuihei.
This area in particular is
called a tohua, which is a
public meeting place, so
anything important that would
happen in tribal life would
happen right here.
You will now serve as
ambassadors to a very important
event in your world, the merging
of your two tribes.
Rotu, Maraamu, no more.
Tonight, the new tribe will be
born under your guidance.
You will sleep under the stars
on the same paepae where rival
chiefs would meet 500 years ago
to discuss and make decisions.
By morning, you will have made
several important decisions,
among them creating the new
tribes' name, and painting the
new tribal flag.
Now because this is a very big
responsibility, we want you guys
to be well fed, so you're
thinking very clearly.
So if you guys will have a seat,
I will go get your food.
>> We got a lot to talk about.
>> Yeah, man.
>> PROBST: Tell me this is not
going to be a fun night.
>> Oh, my God, yes!
>> PROBST: A little more to
come.
>> Thank you!
>> PROBST: Now what would pizza
be without beer!
>> All right!
>> Oh, my God.
Jeff sat us down to pizza and
30 Coors Light.
>> Cheers.
>> I was siting across from this
young buck, and I'm going,
"I'm going to pound beers and
eat pizza with this guy?"
I've heard a lot about you.
>> I've heard a lot about you.
(laughing)
>> So we have to come up with a
name.
>> Bernie's tribe.
>> That's original.
>> I was just on a total high.
I knew that by responding to
this challenge I was taking a
chance, and it paid off.
Pizza and beer!
>> I feel so bad.
My tribe people would love
pizza.
>> I feel bad, too.
>> You do not.
>> That's too bad for them.
>> We started talking
immediately about what's
happening with the tribes.
Zoe and I were like the moms.
You know, we were cleaning up.
We were getting the tribe going.
>> Really.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You and Zoe feel you're
pretty close?
>> Zoe and I were like moms.
"Let's clean the place up."
>> Unreal.
That's unreal.
The lies going on.
Honestly, you feel you're close,
you and Zoe?
>> Zoe?
>> Yeah.
Unreal.
Zoe is funny because I
confronted Zoe.
She told me that she was voting
you off, right, and then I go to
John, I said, "John, who's
next?," and he said, "Kathy."
She doesn't know if I'm telling
the truth or lying, just like I
don't know, just like nobody in
this game knows who's telling
the truth.
>> After talking to Gina, I
thought he was just a lazy kid.
Young, didn't care.
I'm having a hard time with it.
>> What exactly did Gina say
about me that made me out to be
such a bad person that they want
to vote me off so bad now?
>> You're a lazy bum and you
don't care about anything.
>> Really?
>> She thinks you were two-faced
and you were mean.
>> Really.
That's unreal.
>> You're telling me Zoe is
voting me off.
Zoe and I bonded, so you think
that's not a shock to my system?
>> Let me tell you something.
I'm sitting here talking to you
right now, Kathy.
I may be writing my own destiny
up here.
If they find out that I said
anything, then they're going to
take me out and you'll be
second.
Unless we're going to change
that.
You want to make a pact, me and
you?
>> Do you want to?
>> They'll never know.
It will be just me and you.
>> I felt this pact we were
going to form was okay, but it
happened so quickly, and he
wanted it so badly, I just sort
of shook hands.
All right.
>> All right.
>> Let's do it.
>> Serious.
>> All right, I am really
serious.
Don't stab me.
>> You don't have to ask me
twice.
I swear to God, I will never
vote you off.
I promise.
John thinks I have an alliance
with the team.
Now she thinks I have an
alliance with her.
Dude, I've been lying this whole
game.
John thinks he's going to ride
it all the way to the end.
I'm being serious.
>> No, I'm totally agreeing with
you.
I just can't get over how
conniving it is.
>> Who is John, some kind of
Marquesan god?
(laughing)
Have another beer.
>> I'm a little hesitant on why
he just suddenly decided to make
me on as his soulmate or
whatever it is.
It was so quick.
And I just don't trust that
element of it.
We're going to sleep well,
under mosquito netting, my God.
Does that mean that we can sleep
without pants on?
Don't panic.
>> You're crazy.
We can't talk about anything
that's going on.
I basically saw another Sarah in
her for me.
Warm me up, baby.
Want to massage me, baby?
It's going to be interesting
because if I actually do stand
by my word and go with Kathy,
it's a new game.
Will you remember in the morning
that we made an agreement?
>> We made an agreement, buddy.
>> Then in the end it'll be me
and you.
>> That will be a riot.
Let's see if we can do it.
>> Rob and I promised each other
not to tell anybody that we
discussed the tribal issues.
We just were going to tell both
the Rotu members and Maraamu
that the conversation was about
the new tribe name, the flag,
getting to know each other.
>> Don't panic.
Don't be nervous.
>> We came back to Maraamu.
>> Hi, guys!
>> And we had to inform Paschal
and Neleh that we had to get
everything out of the camp onto
a raft in five minutes.
We got five minutes!
Everything we got, come on.
Everything we got.
Everything!
Get the kettles.
Get the knives, Neleh!
>> Put everything on top.
Water jugs, Pappy.
Kathy, help me get it on top
here.
>> We got it. We got it.
Keep going.
>> Let's go.
>> Okay, that's it.
Grapefruits coming down.
>> One minute!
One minute!
(panting)
Everybody back to the raft.
Now, Paschal!
Touch the raft.
Good job, guys.
>> Good job, buddy.
Nice to meet you.
>> Yeah, you too, buddy.
Rob.
Pascal.
Neleh.
>> Oh, my God, we did it.
>> With only four of us we did
it.
We're a team.
All of us.
No, there's a merge.
>> Oh, really.
>> We have so much to talk
about.
>> Here you go, man.
>> So this is our new buff?
(coughing)
>> This is it.
(cheers)
>> Good job, guys.
Unbelievable.
>> You know, upon arriving to
the new tribe, it was great to
see everyone, but I definitely
entered with hesitancy.
>> You're the only person I
didn't give a hug.
>> I know.
Hi, Tam.
Good, I'm tired.
But it's good to see you.
>> You guys also.
>> And I was aloof and trying to
figure it all out after hearing
what Boston Rob told me about
these people wanting to vote me
off.
>> Great seeing you.
>> I was disappointed, too, that
the loyalty's shot.
It's gone.
>> So how you doing, Zoe?
>> What's that?
>> How you doing?
>> Doing better now that you
guys are here.
Here, I'll put this up in a
tree.
I think we got most of it.
I was aloof to Zoe, worried that
she actually was going to vote
me off.
I didn't trust her.
I didn't trust John.
I didn't trust Tammy.
I didn't trust the General.
I didn't trust anybody when I
got back here, really.
I was very, very, aloof and
somewhat quiet, just sort of
hanging on the outer rim.
>> All right.
So these are the new buffs and
the new flags.
>> What's the new name, guys?
>> Yeah, what's the new name?
>> The new name, we had like a
half-hour to make this, this
morning, so.
The name of it is Soliantu.
>> Soliantu.
>> And the name means...
Sacred allegiance to the sun.
>> That's cool, guys.
Yeah!
>> Everybody hold hands.
Soliantu!
>> Ready?
One, two, three.
Soliantu!
>> Let's just get it out of the
way right now.
>> Rob and Kathy together
developed our new name,
Soliantu, and our new flag.
We got our new buffs, pink
buffs.
The women were very happy about
it.
You know, I don't care what they
say.
Real men don't wear pink.
>> What was that?
>> I said real men wear pink.
>> Okay, Rob.
>> Well, when we finally got the
ramp and the supplies on shore,
everybody just like busy little
beavers went right to doing what
they had to do.
>> Reposition.
There we go.
>> We were just so happy to be
back together again.
It was like old times.
>> So we got a harvest here,
Dear Lord, in the name of Jesus,
with new tribe members, new
colors and a new life.
We thank you, Lord, in the name
of Jesus that everyone got here
safely, keep our spirits high,
for we know not what's going to
happen tomorrow.
We give you all the honor, glory
and praise, today and
forevermore, for Solianu.
Soliantu?
Solianu.
>> Soliantu.
One, two, three, Soliantu.
>> The game faces are on in full
tilt and nobody wants to talk
about it.
Weird.
Nobody wants to talk to me about
it.
I think the game has changed in
the sense that the Rotu loyalty
has dissolved or it has taken on
new shape.
And there is definitely some
undercurrent alliance that's
been formed while we were over
at Maraamu.
But in my heart I just can't get
over that this Rotu tribe wanted
to vote me off.
>> I'm about ready to get axed.
>> Eh.
>> No, I'm serious.
I believe it.
So I don't know what to do.
Powerful people on this beach,
if you ask me.
They're playing us, just so you
know.
They're playing you and Neleh
too, and I just want you to
understand that.
>> Oh, I understand that
completely.
>> Yeah.
I think it's time to find out
how we all are playing out in
these people's minds.
Not just sit and wait to get
voted off.
>> Well, when we first landed,
Kathy, I think she may have been
advised by Rob either on the way
over here or sometime shortly
after we got here, that she was
being looked at very closely as
a possible first elimination,
and she was really upset about
it.
I just told Kathy, I said look,
you know, I'll listen and maybe
there's an opportunity that
we'll find ourselves in, and if
I do, I'll let you know.
I just didn't want her to get in
a confrontational mode this
early on after reuniting.
>> By God, it's a game.
But I don't think lying fits
into games.
So just tell me the truth, man,
and keep it upfront because
I just can't deal with lying.
And integrity is critical in
this game, I feel.
So I really appreciate it.
>> Those little white ball
things-- I don't know what those
are called.
>> A couple people said that you
absolutely should not lie to
play this game.
Let's, you know, start something
new.
Let's tell everybody before
they're going to get voted out
and let's not lie, ever.
And you know what, that is just
great, up here.
But it's not realistic.
>> I don't want any bugs
crawling in my ears.
Same here.
>> This is a game about being
the smartest person, outwitting,
outplaying and outlasting
everybody else, and you may have
to tell a white lie along the
way or two or three.
But I went into this game
knowing that I was going to do
what it takes to win the game.
I hope when all is said and done
that these people still look at
me and still like me.
I don't intend to lie to any of
their faces, but I do intend to
play the game and win it.
>> What's up?
Should we have a little talk?
>> Sure.
>> I wanted to talk to you two
privately.
Sure.
>> Branch down here to sit on.
>> I want to talk about a couple
things.
>> Oh...
>> I'm just curious.
Who you guys voting for?
>> I haven't figured my vote.
>> I don't think it's any of
your business, first of all.
>> I find you amazing, Zoe.
>> Excuse me?
>> I find you amazing.
>> Why thank you.
>> I trust you, and everybody is
lying, left and right.
>> You know what it is, it's all
about tribal loyalty.
There's still a ghost of Rotu,
and that's what the problem is.
>> Right, but that wasn't the
way it was supposed to be, was
it, Zoe?
I mean, I thought we had an
agreement, Zoe, you know?
You and I and John and Tammy and
Sean, and Vecepia and Rob.
>> Agreement about?
>> Didn't we have an agreement
about taking everybody from
their side of the island off?
You don't remember anything
about that?
>> No.
>> See, this is what I mean.
Unbelievable.
And Kathy wasn't your first
choice as soon as she got here,
and we promised that if we got
rid of Gabe that we'd stay
together?
>> How did you ever get that?
>> How do I ever get that?
Unbelievable.
Tell the truth, go on, will you?
Tell the truth.
Don't worry, everybody.
I'm telling everybody tonight,
Zoe, everybody.
The other day, didn't you tell
me you were voting for Kathy,
yes or no?
>> No, I didn't.
>> No, you didn't?
You paused and you lied.
I can't say that I didn't see it
coming.
It was like a certain degree of
trust that I felt, among the
group.
And it completely got shattered.
Where you going?
You leaving, Kathy?
>> Yeah, for crying out loud, I
get a story from you and then I
get a story from Zoe and people
are lying through their teeth,
and I haven't lied once, man.
I don't know what this stupid
game is about, but I'm out of
here.
>> You can believe what you want
to believe, okay.
>> I don't like to be lied to,
and then again and again and
again.
It irritates me.
>> Zoe is lying to me.
They're all lying to me.
They're all lying to me,
and I'm being played as a pawn.
A pawn.
I need the immunity because I'm
getting the ax.
I don't know.
It's just not adding up, but I'm
going to trust what Rob told me,
and I need immunity to stay in
the game.
>> PROBST: First things first.
As always, Edgar is coming back.
Let me say, congratulations on
making the merge.
The good news is you now have a
one in ten shot of being the
sole survivor.
Now because we are an individual
immunity, the idol is no more.
This is what you covet.
Since you're now competing
against one another, you have a
chance to win individual
immunity.
Win it, you alone are safe from
the vote.
To win it, you're going to have
to have some good sea legs for
our immunity challenge today.
Each tribe member will stand on
a platform in the water.
The person to stand the longest
without falling off wins.
Only your feet may touch the
platform.
Any other body part touches the
platform, you're out.
You've randomly drawn numbers
for which platform you'll stand
on.
Take your spot on your platform.
Wait for my go.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Immunity at stake.
Survivors ready?
>> Ready.
>> PROBST: Go!
Challenge is on!
Neleh, you touched the platform.
Neleh and General are down.
Neleh, General, take a spot on
the shoreline.
Paschal is down.
>> Watch out.
There you go!
Bye-bye!
>> PROBST: V. is down.
Going to do the backstroke to
the beach.
Zoe, you look very comfortable
out there.
>> Nice recovery, John.
Oh, baby.
>> Come on, Johnny.
>> PROBST: Sorry, Sean, you
touched.
Down to five.
Zoe, you're out.
>> Oh.
>> Hang in there, buddy.
Hang in there.
>> Whoa!
Whoa!
>> He touched it!
>> PROBST: Whoa, Rob.
You're done.
>> Told you about being a wise
ass.
>> Oh, God.
>> Steady foot, John!
>> Go, Johnny, pots and pans.
Baby!
>> PROBST: Tammy goes in head
first.
Take a spot on the shoreline.
We are down to two.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: John and Kathy.
For immunity.
>> So many times he's like
stumbled and he just stay there,
man.
And he hasn't touched once.
He just stays up there.
Kathy is holding in there.
>> Kathy is pretty steady.
Steady.
>> PROBST: Whoa.
John.
Kathy wins immunity.
You lost your concentration,
John.
Kathy.
>> What?
>> PROBST: You want this?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Come get it.
>> All right, baby!
(cheering)
Well earned.
>> PROBST: Turn around here.
Here we go.
>> Yes!
>> It's terrible living over
here with these people.
They're all trying to merge into
one like they're one big happy
family.
The way I see it now, Kathy
probably blabbed to John, ratted
me out.
John's slick, but he's not as
smart as he thinks he is.
See the thing is, you can't have
secrets too long in this game,
especially in an individual
situation like we're in now.
But within the next two Tribal
Councils, John is going to get
exposed one way or another.
I mean, that's the game.
If you can figure out what
buttons to push on what people,
then you're going to have the
advantage.
>> Hey, what's up?
Where you going tonight?
>> I have no idea.
>> I thought we were taking them
out one at a time.
>> There's lots of things we
came up with.
>> What happened about my word
is my bond?
>> Oh, yeah, mine was fine
until you went right to Kathy
and went right over at that
other side and said, "They're
going to vote you out first."
>> I did not say that to Kathy.
>> I'm not going to have this
conversation.
Don't lie to my face.
>> There we go.
Now it's on, man.
Now it's personal.
>> No, no.
You know why it's personal
because you're going to stand
here and act like you didn't
have that conversation.
>> You're over here, Mr. I'm Not
Lying.
>> We had conversations.
We looked each other in the eye,
looked each other in the eye.
And if it would have rested and
it would have stayed still,
then I would have been like fine
with it.
>> So why you didn't come to me
man to man, then, John?
>> Because at that point you
betrayed me.
>> How I betray you?
>> This is too much drama.
>> Obviously, it was a mutual
agreement between everybody.
Now this changed?
>> Dude, how can it be a mutual
agreement?
Each person is an individual,
they get to decide.
>> Why wasn't the individual
vote thrown in when it was
Gabriel's turn to get voted out?
It wasn't individual then.
It was a (blip) alliance of
seven, right?
Don't hand me that individual's
(blip) when Gabe's ass was time
to get out because he didn't
fit into your plan.
So he had to go.
Now we're talking about, well,
everybody got their own vote.
Everybody got their own vote.
You all got a four thing going,
you included us and said, "All
right, we're going to go in
seven."
Everybody was like, "We team.
We team."
>> You flat out said...
>> But I'm saying, don't tell me
one thing and just because I
think about something or just
because I talk to somebody, then
all of a sudden it's off.
>> So wait a minute.
What am I supposed to be?
Like, naive?
>> You're not playing both
sides?
>> I'm not playing both sides,
Rob.
>> It's all right, well,
everything is coming out
tonight, so don't worry.
>> It's already out.
What more do you want?
It's already out.
>> I hope you don't have any
secrets.
This here is getting clean.
>> That's fine.
I'm totally clean, too.
I have no worries.
>> Cool.
>> Rob, you want to vote me out
tonight, vote me out.
But tell me man to man like Gabe
did, okay?
Okay, bud?
Don't go to Kathy and say...
>> I've been true to one person
had this whole thing, me.
I keep my word to me.
>> I hear you.
I hear you.
I keep my word to myself, too.
>> I've told nobody nothing, and
that's the way it is.
>> You haven't told anybody
anything?
>> I made no alliances to you.
I made no alliances to nobody.
I just keep my word to myself.
>> That's what I'm saying.
That's cool.
>> I haven't talked to anybody.
Nobody's talked to me.
Fine, I'm happy.
I do my own thing.
>> That's fine.
If you're telling the truth...
>> I'm The General and that's
that.
>> Cool.
>> It's tough because you're
looking for angles.
You're constantly looking for an
angle to play.
Maybe everybody is lying, you
know.
Who knows?
>> Five years ago, I'd have been
worse than Rob.
I probably wanted to push John
into that freaking fire.
The reason I'm more upset
because I've had personal
one-on-ones with John and we've
self-disclosed stuff.
How it's like to be a black man,
how it's like to be a gay man,
what it's like to be isolated.
We shared moments that got
nothing to do with this game.
And when we share those kind of
moments, and then you come and
try to pull some BS like this,
it's really hurtful.
>> What outfit should I wear
tonight to Tribal Council?
>> Now everybody is back to that
love tribe, happy family thing,
so I didn't expect it to be that
way, but it is.
God only knows how many people
are real about it.
It's flipping me out.
>> Like I said, day one is
completely different than day 21
or whatever.
>> Let's go over it so I feel
better.
Okay, babe.
Thank you.
I just have to keep telling
myself it's a game, and get into
this peculiar act of kissy and
love, and I love you, but guess
what, when we go to the next
Tribal Council, you're out.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Tribal
Council.
Congratulations on making it
this far.
Survive tonight, you are
guaranteed a place in the jury
and a chance to be the sole
Survivor.
Let's start at the top.
V, is it a different mindset
now that it's no longer two
tribes facing off, but it is ten
individuals?
>> Most definitely.
I think it is a different
mindset because you're coming
from competing as a group entity
to competing one-on-one.
So you're no longer looking at
the other person as your
teammate per se, but looking at
each and every one of these as
our adversary.
I mean, they're all our great
friends, but this is my
adversary now.
This is my adversary now, but we
love each other very much.
>> PROBST: Sean, what's the mood
of this tribe?
>> I feel like the outsider,
quite frankly, because it is an
old reunion of old tribe
members.
I can't speak for Maraamu right
now is a mixture of emotions,
right now, because I'm fighting
for my life individually, since
I came over, I felt like.
>> PROBST: Zoe, how do you
respond to Sean feeling like,
you know what, I don't have a
shot in hell right now, because
you guys all have a pact and no
matter what I do, no matter how
I contribute, you'll never let
me in the group?
>> Well, I don't think that's
necessarily the case.
Everybody has their own feelings
about, you know, how strong they
feel within our family and our
tribe.
And if that's the way Sean
feels, I feel sorry for him
feeling that way, but if that's
the way he feels, I don't see
that.
>> PROBST: How about you,
General?
What's your point of view on how
far you'll go in this game?
>> I'll never do anything to
compromise my values.
You know, I am who I am, and I,
you know, my word is my bond.
I'm not a youngster.
You know, my word is all I got.
>> PROBST: John, same for you?
I think you've told me that, you
know, I'm going to tell you the
way it is.
>> My personal rule is that, you
know, if somebody wants to have
a bond with me or whatever you
want to call it, fine.
Come talk to me, and if I agree
to it, that's great.
If you come to me and say one
thing, and you agree to it, and
then you immediately turn around
and start adjusting it without
telling me you're adjusting it,
to me that's the same as lying.
>> PROBST: How about you, Rob?
Are you happy with the way you
played?
>> I'm happy with the way I've
play the game.
>> PROBST: Have you lied?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Anybody else here
lied to you?
>> Without a doubt people have
lied to me.
People that are sitting here
telling you right now that they
have not lied, they have lied.
Those people know who they are.
I don't feel it's necessary to
one by one single them out, but
I think people need to be able
to look in the mirror at
themselves after and if they're
happy with the way they played
the game, that's fair enough for
me.
>> PROBST: All right.
There's a new facet now to
immunity, now that we've reached
the individual stage, and it
works like this.
When you win immunity, you now
own immunity, and you can assign
that immunity to somebody else.
So if you feel very secure, you
can buy a favor, you can buy
somebody's vote, you can protect
somebody if you want simply by
giving your immunity to them.
Kathy, you didn't have the
luxury of negotiating today.
So I'll put you on the spot now.
And are you secure enough now to
give that immunity to somebody
else?
>> After what I went through
today?
I do not feel secure.
Because I feel that there were
some really strange things that
happened today with deceit and
lies that I'll talk to people
about it and hopefully get it
resolved, but I question the
whole loyalty thing.
It evaporated.
So the immunity to me right now
is important.
>> PROBST: It's time to vote.
Kathy is the only one safe from
the vote.
Neleh, you're first.
>> Boston Rob, I'm voting for
you, boy.
You tried to stir up a lot of
stuff today.
I knew from the beginning that
you weren't going to keep your
word.
You attacked me personally, so
I'm more than happy to put this
in here for you.
>> I vote for Johnny.
You play the game real well.
Hopefully, if things swing
right, you'll be gone.
If not we'll see you on the flip
side.
>> Yo, look here, man.
I'm voting for you because you
dissed me and my boy, and if I
get voted out next, I really
don't give a damn.
But your time is coming.
You definitely lied to us.
That's for me and you, dawg.
>> My vote tonight is for Rob
Mariano.
Brother, you know, we came into
this tribe with not the right
numbers, so we were kind of
down.
But I know soon I'll have to set
up that debt for the Maraamu
tribe and give you guys all
pizza and beer.
I'm looking forward to it.
See you soon.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Rob.
John.
Three votes Rob, two votes John.
Zoe.
Four votes Rob, two votes John,
one vote Zoe.
Rob.
That's five.
Seventh person voted out of the
tribe: Boston Rob.
No need to read the last vote.
Rob, the tribe has spoken.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Well, you've made it
21 days.
You've reached the final nine,
which means the fate of two of
you rests in the hands of the
others.
And from what I heard tonight,
should make for a very
interesting final 18 days.
You guys can head back to camp.
See you tomorrow.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Kathy confronts Zoe about her
lying ways.
>> There was never any intention
of voting you off.
>> Zoe just lied to me
point-blank.
>> The Survivors reach new
heights.
Fly!
Neleh gets upset with the
actions of some of her tribe
mates.
>> I've been nothing but honest
to everybody.
I'm following my heart.
There's got to be something
changed here.
>> I like people to know that
this was a game, and I hope
everybody doesn't take so much
of everything that I said
seriously.
I was trying to be funny.
It's just my personality.
I definitely enjoyed the game.
I like trying to manipulate more
than anything else.
I hope nobody comes away with
any bad feelings afterwards.
I hope we can all be friends.