>> PROBST: 24 days ago, 16
castaways were marooned in the
middle of one of the most remote
places on Earth, the Marquesas,
part of Tahiti's mystical
islands.
The eight remaining members of
the Soliantu tribe have now made
it past the halfway point, each
one now has a one in eight
chance of winning a million
dollars.
Tonight, in a special edition of
highlights and never-before-seen
footage, we'll take a closer
look at their adventure thus
far.
>> This was my luxury item.
It was a voodoo doll, so we're
going to put the other team's
name on it and start jabbing the
hell out of it.
>> (singing in Spanish)
>> These three new members
brought, I guess, a sense humor
that I don't think we had
before, and it was fun.
>> We wanted a word that we can
shout out when we win, and
sounds good.
>> Today is the last day we will
ever get a fair chance.
>> If we make a pact that we're
going to go in firestorm...
Obviously, when Paschal and
Neleh started to see what I've
been talking about all along,
so now the new agreement we have
is that we're going to vote John
out tonight.
>> PROBST: Day 1 found 16
strangers marooned thousands of
miles from the nearest
continent.
As two separate tribes, Maraamu
and Rotu, they found themselves
paddling the rough waters of the
South Pacific, looking for their
camps.
But for some, the journey was
nothing like they expected.
>> If we see the flag, then
we'll just go right.
>> We got to go around that
little jutty thing there.
>> When we first jumped off the
boat there was definitely a lot
of excitement going through
everybody's head.
In the beginning it's all fun,
and then you're paddling for
about ten, 15 minutes, and
reality sets in.
It hits you that there's nobody
here to help you.
The fact of the matter is you
really have to get there.
>> Which way we going? Left?
>> Yeah.
>> It looks like a beach in
there.
>> Rocky beach, though.
Rocky beach.
Take it out.
Look at it.
It's a rocky beach.
>> It looked like according to
the map it would take us maybe
15, 20 minutes, if we were
lucky.
But then once we saw the points
of where we were actually going
ahead of us, that was an insane
distance.
It was very scary.
>> PROBST: The Maraamu tribe's
arrival was nothing short of
majestic.
>> Sarah's arrival was almost
like Cleopatra.
It was like the servants are
paddling and lifting, and she's
sitting on the crate, looking so
marvelous with her boobs hanging
out and her Goldielocks in the
air.
>> Land ho!
Save it.
You know, this is Survivor.
Ain't nobody trying to look at
you like that here.
>> Home sweet home.
>> PROBST: Rotu's arrival was a
joyous one.
>> Woo!
We made it!
>> PROBST: Until they discovered
that their crate held a minimal
amount of supplies.
>> Yeah!
Oh, it's not as much as we
thought!
>> The stuff that was in the
crate: we got a map to our spot.
We got two pots and a pan, two
machetes and a small knife and
then a magnifying glass.
>> PROBST: And starting a fire
became an exercise in futility.
>> It's working.
>> PROBST: But at Maraamu, it
was a different story.
>> People know that I'm into
yoga, and in yoga you breathe
from the diaphragm, so I was
able to take nice, long deep
breaths.
>> PROBST: Using Peter's
breathing technique, Maraamu
quickly had fire.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Keep it going.
Keep it going.
>> As night fell on Maraamu, Rob
and Sarah were immediately drawn
to one another.
>> Is it comfy?
>> Oh, yeah, it's like a
waterbed.
>> Oh, cool.
>> Dude, I could go to sleep
right now.
>> Last night there was
definitely flirtation around Rob
and Sarah.
>> We fill this thing up and let
it cook in the sun all day
tomorrow.
>> There you go.
>> We get a hot tub.
>> That's an idea.
>> They got into the raft that
we had paddled in on,
and they kind just hung out away
from everybody else, and, you
know, were there pretty much the
whole entire night.
So at that point, I'm now, that
was another, you know, question.
Well, what are they saying, you
know, are they flirting or are
they making an alliance?
>> PROBST: As the sun rose on
the morning of Day 2, Kathy
was still determined to start a
fire.
>> This is the most important
thing right now.
So we need to get a group
dynamic.
>> How many hours I spent
yesterday, I'm wiped.
>> How many hours did you spend
yesterday?
>> You tell me.
>> Not many.
I don't think we spent more than
two.
>> PROBST: John, for the sake of
tribal harmony, decided to work
on the fire himself.
>> That's nice.
>> Yes!
>> We got fire!
>> Fire!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: The tribes received
their first tree mail.
>> Oh, no, we're on the water!
>> PROBST: And Rotu planned on
sticking it to Maraamu in the
first immunity challenge.
>> This was my luxury item,
a voodoo doll.
So we're going to put the other
team's name on it and start
jabbing the hell out of it.
Pass it around.
Everybody gets a shot.
>> I'll get their swimming feet.
>> I'm going for the shoulder in
case we're rowing.
>> It won't go in his head.
>> I'll stick it in the arm and
hopefully their arm will be
sore.
>> PROBST: At the challenge, the
tribes were told they would be
entirely on their own.
In addition to no food, no
water, you're getting no fire
help from us at all, of any kind
at any time.
Survivors ready?!
Go!
>> Woo!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Rotu easily won.
And on Day 3, the game became a
harsh reality, as Maraamu
realized they had to vote out
one of their own.
>> My strategy is to keep the
strong as strong as possible.
>> Peter got on our nerves a
little bit this morning because
he came up and called us all
over and wanted us to talk about
what the strategy of the game
was and how he was going to do
it.
>> I'm not this magical mystical
person, all right.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I think if you want to get
the truth on the situation,
right, you just can look in
someone's eyes.
That's not like, "Ooh."
>> Some people are going to look
you in the eye and lie to you,
though.
>> I know you don't have an
alliance.
>> I mean, an alliance right now
means absolutely nothing.
>> I don't know that.
>> There is no alliance here.
>> Right now the game has
shifted from survival to a
paranoia state.
I believe that Peter has taken
it to the extreme.
>> I can see the faces, and I
know the, you know, I know the
outcome of tonight's vote.
>> You don't know what you're
talking about.
From based on what people are
looking?
People are tired.
People are hungry.
>> It's better for me to talk
about it because I won't be able
to talk to you tonight.
>> PROBST: Even though Patricia
and Sarah received votes,
Peter's instincts were correct.
He was the first person voted
out.
First person voted out of the
tribe: Peter.
The tribe has spoken.
On Day 4, the mood at Maraamu
was upbeat.
The tribe awoke to Sean's radio
program.
>> You got today's weather
report, Hunter?
Hold on.
Let me change the station.
>> Hunter Ellis with today's
morning weather!
>> PROBST: At Rotu it was all
work and no play.
Until Kathy found food.
(whistling)
>> Hey, you guys, get over here!
I'm serious!
>> We got seven.
One, two, three, four.
>> Whoa, that was slimy.
>> I know, but a lot of meat
here.
A lot of protein we're looking
at.
>> PROBST: And to flavor up
their meal, Gabe added some
spice to the mix.
>> These are peppers.
>> Peppers!
>> Way to go, guys.
>> Ah!
>> Coconut, lime and peppers.
>> Put in some more peppers.
>> That looks yummy.
>> Wow! Wow!
God, that's good.
>> PROBST: Back at Maraamu, Rob
was trying out some inventive
cooking of his own.
>> I'm going to fry up a little
papaya.
I have no idea how this is going
to turn out.
>> I'm not going to eat it until
you eat it.
It's your concoction.
>> It's pretty good.
It tastes like...
warm papaya.
>> What do you think?
>> PROBST: But Patricia wanted
to get the chores done.
>> Here's the plan: you all get
ready and go gather some
coconuts, and we're going to
finish getting these flat rocks.
>> How can we get coconuts
without a stick?
>> Well, he'll get you a stick.
He's a great stick hunter.
>> Work needs to get done and if
somebody is not going to step up
to the plate, I don't mind
telling somebody, "Look, let's
go."
>> First it was endearing
because it just seemed natural.
Now it just seemed like, "Oh,
no, Mama got to work.
Mama can't sit down."
>> Now listen to me, I'm only
going to tell you this once.
>> I heard it this morning
already once.
>> Tool tree.
>> I already heard it.
I know.
I know everything needs to go
back where you find it.
I know.
>> I'm tired of trying to...
>> Where's the knife then?
>> PROBST: On Day 5, the tribes
competed for some valuable
fishing gear.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Mask, snorkel, fins.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?!
Go!
Rotu!
(cheering)
Rotu won the mask and fins, but
there were more victories to
come.
>> What do we got today?
>> Oh, my God, it's a fork.
>> PROBST: Getting a utensil in
the mail on Day 6 could only
mean one thing.
>> A food challenge.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: And it was.
The tribes had to eat ...
a Marquesan delicacy of fish
soaking in fermented sea water.
Rob choked and Maraamu lost
their third challenge in a row.
So Maraamu headed back to Tribal
Council, where in a 4-3 vote,
Patricia, known as the tribe's
mom, was voted out.
Patricia, the tribe has spoken.
Maraamu lost their second tribe
member.
It's time for you to go.
Day 7 would prove to be a lesson
in pain for Rotu.
While snorkeling for food, John
was the first victim.
>> I landed right on top of a
sea urchin, and embedded about
12 sea urchin needles in my
fingers.
I got to go back in and get
somebody to pee on it.
That's what you're supposed to
do from that kind of a venomous
sting from a sea urchin is to
urinate on it.
I need somebody who can pee on
my hand.
Someone have to go to the
bathroom?
>> PROBST: Luckily, someone did.
>> I didn't even think it was
weird that she was squatting
down and I had my hand between
her legs.
>> Good thing you had to go to
the bathroom.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: On Day 8, bamboo
and rope were delivered to the
tribes.
>> To what do we owe this honor?
>> PROBST: I come bearing
supplies for your next
challenge.
At Rotu, the tribe was dealt a
painful blow again.
>> A big rock got in between my
shoe and my foot and just sliced
up my toe nicely.
>> PROBST: And again.
>> John actually stuck his hand
underneath a rock and an eel bit
him.
>> Oh, my God.
What is going on?
(shouting)
>> PROBST: But not even injuries
could stop a closely-knit Rotu
tribe as they beat Maraamu in a
tight finish in the reward
challenge.
Rotu!
>> Ready to rock?
>> Everybody wants to go.
>> PROBST: Maraamu set out for a
hike on Day 9.
>> Patricia went for a hike one
day by herself, found a stream
on the other side of the hill,
so I think that could be
something that we need to go
check out.
It's also a good opportunity for
us all to get out and do
something together as a tribe.
>> Is the creek definitely down
there?
>> It ends down there.
It's pretty direct.
It's just it's steep.
>> This is doing a whole lot for
me.
I thought it was an easy walk to
the creek.
>> It comes right out of the
rocks, a little bit to this side
of where I think the river is
going to come out.
>> But after all of this, we're
going to spend ten minutes and
leave?
>> And then climb back up?
>> Hunter, he's just up and
always busy, the thing is we
didn't come here to exert
ourselves in this tropical heat.
Damn all this other work.
We need energy to get those damn
challenges.
>> PROBST: Go!
In the immunity challenge, the
tribes battled it out in a
coconut maze race.
>> In the hole, here we go!
Yeah!
>> PROBST: Maraamu lost yet
again.
So Rob strategized behind the
scenes and became the tribe's
puppet master.
>> It's important for me to have
people on my team that are going
to do what I tell them to do.
Game always keeps you thinking.
It really does.
Fear keeps people loyal.
If they're afraid they have
something to lose, then they'll
do what they tell you to do.
That's straight out of The
Godfather.
It's true.
>> PROBST: It was a shocking
Tribal Council, as Maraamu voted
out the strongest member of
their tribe.
Hunter, the tribe has spoken.
First step: pick a disk.
Doesn't matter.
It's totally random.
Follow your gut.
Go wherever you want.
On Day 10 the tribes came
together for the biggest twist
in the game yet.
Okay.
Zoe, you're first.
Step off your disk.
Pull off your new buff.
Take your old one off.
Put your new one on.
The tribes were randomly
switched up.
Some friendships remained
together.
>> Yeah! Pappy's on our team.
>> We got Pappy.
>> PROBST: While others were
torn apart.
Rob, you're now a member of
Rotu.
Sarah.
All right, Sarah, same buff,
still a member of Maraamu.
But for the remaining 13
survivors, all bets were off.
It was time to play a brand-new
game.
At Maraamu, Kathy, Paschal, and
Neleh were pleased with their
new camp.
>> That forest is so beautiful.
>> Well, let's show you guys
around.
>> This is a breadfruit.
This is a mango tree.
>> All you got to do is pick up
the limes off the ground.
>> I just got off of a tribe
that would get up at dawn, check
the pig pit, you know, and go
out and forage for shells.
So to us, we feel like it was a
four-star hotel and that there's
fruit on the table, so it was
pretty nice.
>> PROBST: For the new members
of Rotu, life seemed pleasant as
well.
They were ecstatic when they saw
their new water source.
>> Yeah!
>> It is so, so good.
>> I didn't even know what else
to say.
>> I'm loving it.
>> Good, I'm glad to hear it.
>> I am loving it.
>> Now they see this, I'm like,
hey, you know, this ain't too
bad.
(singing)
>> PROBST: On Day 11, Sean
introduced his new tribe to the
radio program.
>> Girl, you know you...
(singing)
>> When we landed here on Rotu
camp, we told them about some of
the things that we did on our
camp, like the early morning
show, and they were more than
willing to try it.
>> No longer are they down with
the Maraamu, we could never say
our name right, so I'm not going
to say it right this morning.
>> Rotu can do!
>> That's right: Rotu can do.
And we're going to head over and
get a food report from our main
chef, Johnny Pots and Pans.
>> At first I thought we might
all start off with a little raw
coconut, and if we go searching
pretty hard, we might find
ourselves some sea urchins, but
watch those spines.
Back to you.
>> These three new members
brought I guess a sense of humor
that I don't think we had
before, and it was fun.
>> Why don't you give us an
overall report on things on this
island.
How are things going on the
Marquesan Islands?
>> (with Australian accent):
Well, we're all settling in to
our new habits, looking for a
new place to hang up some
clothes, find a place to sleep,
all try to get together.
I'm sure we can do it in the
speed of the Thames here.
I'm sure we can pull through in
the end.
Back to you, Rock.
>> They seemed like they enjoyed
it.
We all can sit around and have
fun and laugh and bond in other
ways than just working.
>> The in people will be
sporting lovely new buffs.
You can wrap them around your
head in any manner whatsoever.
>> You can sit down and
self-disclose yourself and
laugh, and seemed like the radio
show was well received.
That concludes our wake-up show
for this morning.
Stay tuned tomorrow same time,
same station.
We'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a good day, and remember,
God loves you.
>> PROBST: The two new tribes
squared off against each other
in an immunity challenge on Day
12.
Today's immunity challenge is
all about the weaving.
Each of you have a woven
tapestry that is scrambled.
It's very simple.
The first tribe to unscramble it
correctly wins immunity.
Losing tribe: Tribal Council
tonight with me.
But Rotu continued to function
like a well-oiled machine, and
they beat Maraamu again.
>> Here it comes.
>> That's it.
That's it.
That's it right there.
>> PROBST: Rotu!
>> Rotu!
>> Yes!
>> All right!
>> PROBST: So the new Maraamu
headed to Tribal Council, where
the old Rotu members, along with
Gina, voted Sarah out.
Sarah, the tribe has spoken.
Paranoia swept over Rotu on Day
13, and John became suspicious
when Gabe said he wasn't there
to play the game.
>> What are the ethics in this
game?
>> To me it's tell the truth.
Be honest.
Are you saying that you would
lie to win this game?
>> I'm not even here to play the
game, man.
>> Gabriel said he's not playing
the game.
I just, I don't believe it.
I mean, you are here to play
this game.
You're not here on a commune.
You know, this is not the '60s
and, you know, free love and all
that kind of stuff.
>> PROBST: To solidify his
position, John decided to create
an alliance with Tammy, the
General and Zoe, with Gabe to be
their first victim.
>> Basically, I want four people
that I know will not vote for
me, just plain and simple.
So what we're shooting for is
the final four is myself, you
Tammy and Rob.
Just voting as bloc.
Trust me 100%.
I mean, I don't even know what
else I can say to you.
Split my hand open and rub blood
on you.
I mean, I have your back.
I mean, you are, you are my
partner.
>> You swear you're not playing
me.
>> Tammy, on my mother's (blip)
life.
>> If you're playing me, I swear
I'll kick your ass.
>> PROBST: At Maraamu, the
little tribe of four was a huge
underdog.
>> Heavenly Father, we're very
grateful for this wonderful day
that we have ahead of us and we
ask thee if thou would please
help us find all the things that
we need to today.
That we may be able to work hard
together as team.
>> I think we all have a spirit
and it's here.
This is our time now.
>> PROBST: Gina was correct.
It was their time.
At the reward challenge the tiny
Maraamu tribe emerged
victorious.
>> Hurry!
Hurry.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Maraamu!
Maraamu won the opportunity to
get back into the game.
Their reward: a two-minute raid
of Rotu's camp.
Go!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Raid is over.
>> Forgot this!
>> Should have taken the frying
pan.
>> PROBST: By Day 14, John
wasn't certain he had the votes
to oust Gabe, and went to Sean
to secure his vote.
>> I need at least one of the
other new members so I didn't
get myself caught in a tie, in
case Gabe figured out that I was
trying to vote him out.
Planning to vote Gabe tomorrow,
but I did want to know that if
we lose that, you're not going
home.
>> Okay.
>> Okay, but you have to be
tight.
You have to keep your mouth
quiet.
>> I think it was a mistake that
John told me that.
If they're going to vote for
Gabriel, they needed to just do
it and let me sit there and
think that I was going to be
next.
All I'm saying is, stay tuned.
>> PROBST: The immunity
challenge required the tribes to
build an SOS signal.
>> Put one in each corner.
>> Even though it looks like Fat
Albert and the Cosby kids' SOS
sign, it still, I think it's
pretty good, considering what we
have.
>> I made him wear a hat today
because he looks like a pilgrim
boy.
Look at him.
>> All right, guys, this is it!
>> PROBST: The little mouse
tribe of Maraamu roared again.
>> By waving the American flag
as part of their distress
signal...
>> Blow your horn!
>> PROBST: Maraamu finally won
immunity.
(horn blowing)
>> All right!
(cheering)
Yeah!
>> PROBST: Knowing that Gabe was
the target of Rotu's alliance,
Rob approached Gabe in the hopes
of having him vote against John.
>> My only question I have for
you is, if you were 100% set in
the way you wanted to play the
game.
Definitely a twist, the way we
shake things out.
>> Rob Mariano was explaining
that it was probably going to be
me voted out tonight.
Rob wanted to know if I would
make an alliance with him and
Sean and V, and change the tide.
>> PROBST: But in the end, Gabe
was true to his word.
He wasn't there to play the
game.
He was only there for the
experience.
And everyone else was there to
play the game, and Gabe was
voted out.
It's time for you to go.
On Day 16, Maraamu was one happy
little family.
>> I feel stupid that we can't
catch a fish.
Oh look! I love it.
>> Kathy and I were talking
about how I want to go back to
grad school and, you know, do
some things and how she's going
back to school, and we talked
about my dream job.
>> What's your dream job?
>> My dream job is to have a
cabin restaurant, like a
made-out, like a log cabin
restaurant, in Alaska.
>> Gina, she's so aspiring for
dreams.
She's bone honest, sweet,
hardworking, incredible work
ethic, and driven.
>> I would come out and greet
everybody and give them free
coffee.
>> Gina, I think it's a great
idea.
>> Every once in a while maybe
I'd make some homemade biscuits.
>> I want you to be there now,
though.
You could do it.
You could make it happen.
>> She was saying I got to do it
now.
You know, you got to do your
dream job now or it won't
happen.
>> When you hear somebody that's
got that much energy for an
idea, you should implement it
now.
You can always go back to
school.
>> I just don't have the money.
>> It would be great to have her
find her dream.
Then you can help out with the
wildlife area.
>> That would be awesome.
>> You should do it.
>> It was relaxing for me.
Felt like I was talking to a
really good friend about what I
wanted to do with my life.
>> PROBST: At the start of the
reward challenge, Maraamu was
astonished to discover that Gabe
had been voted out.
>> They voted Gabe off.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?!
Go!
>> Come on.
Rob, stop, stop, stop.
>> PROBST: You're still in this.
Let's go.
>> Come on, you guys!
>> Good job.
Come on, guys!
>> Okay, sharp, sharp, sharp.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Against all odds, the
tiny tribe beat Rotu yet again.
Maraamu wins.
Feast.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: And sat down to a
picnic lunch.
>> Oh, my God, it's a picnic!
>> I love picnics.
>> PROBST: On Day 17, the stress
of losing three challenges in a
row reached a boiling point, and
Rob Mariano called attention to
the Rotu alliance.
>> You, The General, Tammy and
John, you guys don't have an
alliance, the four of you?
>> We have a friendship, not an
alliance.
>> That's interesting.
I knew she was lying the second
she told it to me.
I could just tell.
You're telling me straight up
that you four don't have an
alliance, you four over here?
>> How could you say that we
don't, I mean, you'd have to be
blind not to see that.
>> Zoe just told me straight up
in my face not even five minutes
ago, John.
>> Maybe she's not thinking that
way.
Hey.
>> Have I ... you so far?
>> John, do I have "stupid"
written on my forehead?
>> If there's a traditional
merge and we all merge today,
three of them and seven of us,
those three go first.
That is my absolute word.
>> PROBST: John, Rob and Sean
agreed that if the tribes merged
they would vote out the members
of Maraamu first.
>> Don't try to (blip) me.
>> I won't.
I promise.
>> I'm taking your word.
>> I will.
Okay.
>> Same thing, buddy.
>> I think to a degree I may
have convinced him that I'm part
of the team now.
I want him to trust me, but he
shouldn't.
>> PROBST: But Rob still felt
his neck was on the line going
into the next immunity.
>> This immunity challenge is
critical to me.
If we don't win this challenge,
then I'm probably gone tomorrow.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?!
Go!
Rob stepped up, took charge of
the Rotu tribe, and came up with
a huge victory.
Rotu wins!
>> This is it!
That's what it's all about here.
>> PROBST: On Day 18, the family
of Maraamu had to face their
toughest decision, but in the
end, old tribal lines held fast.
>> Gina, I'm taking you to
Alaska and I'm going to get that
restaurant for you.
>> PROBST: And Gina was the
sixth person voted off the
island.
Gina.
The tribe has spoken.
>> Mail call.
>> PROBST: On Day 19, tree mail
instructed both tribes to send
one member on a journey.
Kathy and Rob met at an ancient
paepae, where they were told
that the two tribes were being
merged into one.
Tonight the new tribe will be
born under your guidance.
They celebrated with pizza and
beer.
But the partying soon turned to
more important conversation.
>> Zoe and I were like the moms.
You know, we're cleaning up.
>> Really?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You and Zoe feel you're
pretty close?
>> Zoe and I were like moms.
"Let's clean the place up."
>> Unreal.
>> Yeah.
>> It's unreal, the lies going
on.
She told me that she was voting
you off.
What exactly did Gina say about
me that made me out to be such a
bad person that they want to
vote me off so bad now?
>> You're a lazy bum and you
don't care about anything.
>> Really?
>> PROBST: With this new
information, Kathy and Rob felt
vulnerable.
They decided they would never
vote against each other.
>> Do you want to make a pact,
me and you?
>> Do you want to?
>> They'll never know.
It will be just me and you.
>> All right.
>> All right, let's do it.
>> PROBST: The next morning,
Kathy and Rob awoke for
breakfast.
>> This morning was amazing.
Not only was it just being on
that pillow so wonderful, and
having soft cushions under my
body, when I woke up I saw a
tray of food, I just felt it was
a dream, I truly did.
>> This is out of control.
They're donuts.
>> They're donuts?
>> Pastries.
Well, to the new tribe, new
beginning.
>> Yes.
>> We really pounded out a name
for our new tribe.
Soliantu.
Soliantoo.
Soliantus.
We took the sun, and we took the
word "alliance," and we took the
word "sacred," and we wanted to
use those three words and then
we also wanted a word that we
can shout out when we win, and
it sounds good.
>> Soliantu.
Sacred alliance of sun and fire.
>> That looks pretty cool, you
know that?
>> Yeah, it does.
>> Teamwork.
>> Kathy was awesome company.
We named the new tribe, painted
a new flag, and we got
everything done we needed to get
done.
I just had a wonderful time.
>> What a wonderful, wonderful
night.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: They returned to
Maraamu, where they told Neleh
and Paschal they had five
minutes to load their supplies
onto their raft.
>> We got five minutes.
We got to get everything we got
on the raft!
>> Everything!
>> Come on-- everything we got!
Everything!
Get the kettle.
Get the knives, Neleh!
Touch the raft!
>> You did it.
>> There were only four of us
and we did it.
We're a team, all of us.
There's a merge.
No, there's a merge.
>> Oh, really?
>> We have so much to talk
about.
Here you go, man.
>> Okay, so this is our new
buff?
>> This is it.
>> Here.
>> PROBST: Greeted by the
members of Rotu, Rob handed out
the new buffs and displayed the
new flag.
>> What's the new name, guys?
Cool.
>> Soliantu.
And that name means...
I can't remember.
I keep forgetting.
>> It has all of our initials.
Sacred allegiance to the sun.
>> Sacred allegiance to the sun.
>> Good job.
>> Yeah!
>> Soliantu!
>> One, two, three, Soliantu!
>> PROBST: But the good cheer
and camaraderie at Soliantu
disappeared on Day 21, when Rob
confronted Zoe.
>> Zoe, you didn't have an
agreement about taking everybody
from their side of the island
off?
You don't remember anything
about that?
>> No.
>> See, this is what I mean.
Unbelievable.
And Kathy wasn't your first
choice as soon as she got here?
Tell the truth, for once, will
you?
Tell the truth.
>> PROBST: Kathy, disillusioned
and angry, fled to the
waterfall.
>> Zoe's lying to me.
They're all lying to me.
They're all lying to me, and I'm
being played as a pawn.
A pawn.
I need the immunity because I'm
getting the ax.
I don't know.
It's just not adding up, but I'm
going to trust what Rob told me
and I need immunity to stay in
the game.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?!
Go!
Out-balancing the others on an
unsteady platform in the rough
surf, Kathy won immunity.
Kathy wins immunity.
You want this?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Come get it.
>> All right, baby!
>> PROBST: Turn around here.
(cheering)
Yes!
Back at Soliantu, Rob accused
John of backing out on his word.
>> What happened about my word
is my bond?
>> Oh, yeah, mine was like fine,
but as soon as you double-
tracked and circled back and
came up with other ideas, then
it's like I'm done.
>> PROBST: But John accused Rob
of breaking their agreement when
Rob spoke to Kathy.
>> Don't tell me one thing and
just because I think about
something or just because I talk
to somebody, then all of a
sudden it's off.
>> To be honest I'm not going to
have this conversation.
I'm not going to decide for
myself until we get there
tonight.
>> I thought we had an
agreement.
>> We did, until you went to
Kathy and told her at the other
side, and said they're going to
vote you out first.
>> I did not say that.
>> I'm not going to have this
conversation.
Don't lie to my face.
>> There we go.
Now it's on, man.
>> PROBST: In the end, all the
drama in camp brought about
Rob's demise.
Even Rob's former Maraamu
ally, Vecepia, wrote his name
down at the voting booth.
Rob, the tribe has spoken.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: The next day, Kathy
confronted Zoe.
>> There was never any intention
of voting you off, no way in
hell.
We wanted to get Rotu back
together as a team.
>> Zoe just lied to me
point-blank about the fact that
the tribe had definitely scoped
me out for the first vote off
when we merged.
Oh, my God, look, you guys.
>> PROBST: The tribe received
materials to build kites for the
next reward challenge.
>> Too much wind.
>> Oh, my kite is going to be a
miserable failure.
>> Oh, stop it.
>> I'm serious.
>> Oh, go fly a kite.
>> PROBST: So they did.
Run, John run!
Competing for the chance to have
a Snickers bar and then go scuba
diving, the survivors attempted
to fly their kites into the
Marquesan sky, but it was Kathy
who went the distance.
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
Woo!
>> PROBST: Underwater, Kathy
experienced the serene world of
Marquesan marine life.
On land things weren't as
peaceful, as Sean fought for his
survival.
>> I get frustrated because I
feel like nobody is playing the
game, and I feel like we've kind
of succumbed, and let the four
people run the show.
>> I telling you, I'm going to
talk with Kathy.
>> I totally agree with you.
I think Tammy and John are
playing a game and they're
playing it so hard, it's
obnoxious.
>> If you're in agreement, me
you and V are on the same
wavelength.
>> Yeah, we are.
But we just need to get Paschal
and Neleh.
And you know what, I think we
can do it.
>> My boy.
>> PROBST: On Day 24, the
immunity challenge was a game of
elimination, but Sean, Vecepia
and Kathy saw it as the
alliance's arrogant display of
the pecking order, showing who
they would be voting out next.
>> This is the order of how it's
going to go.
>> Way to go.
>> I swear we could take them
out.
I swear we could.
>> PROBST: Tammy won immunity,
and she, John, Zoe and the
General openly celebrated their
victory.
>> I almost was going to do you
because I hated to get Paschal
another time.
>> It didn't seem to bother you
that much.
>> PROBST: Neleh and Paschal
were also angered by the
arrogant conduct the foursome
had displayed during the
challenge.
>> There was a pecking order and
we were included in it, even
though we were told that that
wasn't true.
>> PROBST: And decided to take
matters into their own hands.
>> I'm not going to go out fifth
or sixth.
We've worked too hard.
>> PROBST: In the shelter,
Vecepia apologized to Sean for
siding with the alliance and
voting against Rob.
>> They came to me, six or seven
days after we were here and told
me they wanted to be part of the
fivesome, and I said if you do
not lie to me, I will go five
with you, and then once we get
the five, it's every man for
themselves.
>> I just wish you had trusted
your brother a little more.
You saw what they did to me and
Rob.
I said these guys were...
>> Exactly.
If I've done wrong with you, I
apologize.
I'm saying this right here and
now.
Straight up, I apologize to you.
>> PROBST: With Vecepia on
board, the fivesome decided
somebody needed to be done.
>> Today is the last day we will
ever get a fair chance.
After that it's going to be four
and four.
It's going to be up for vote and
it's just the way I feel, you
guys, right now, and I'm being
honest with you.
>> Obviously, Paschal and Neleh
started to see what I've been
talking about all along, that
the four horsemen have an
alliance.
They've been switching on and
off, first with me and Rob,
then with her and Paschal.
So now the new agreement we have
is myself and Neleh, V, Paschal,
and Kathy are going to vote John
out tonight.
>> PROBST: That night at Tribal
Council, they struck back.
The eight person voted out, the
first member of our jury: John.
You need to bring me your torch.
The alliance of John, Tammy, Zoe
and the General was broken when
John was voted out of the tribe.
The tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Good night.
John was the eighth person to
go, but he will return as the
first member of the jury which
will ultimately decide who will
be the sole Survivor.
Over the next 15 days, the
Soliantu tribe will experience
the culture and the game in ways
unlike any survivors before
them.
Join us as the adventure
continues.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: John's departure
marks a new era at Soliantu.
>> It's a new day we're starting
here!
Friends become bitter enemies.
>> From the get-go I didn't like
you.
>> I have changed my opinion of
Zoe.
Zoe is a bitch.
>> PROBST: And two lucky
survivors get away from it all.
Now for the reward:
an authentic Marquesan feast.
>> Give me the radio right
there.
It's the wake-up show.
Rah!
Good morning, ladies
and gentlemen.
Good morning.
>> Ding, ding, ding.