>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, the Soliantu camp
embraced a new spirit.
>> This is a new day we're
starting here!
>> The people that play this
game fairly have a good chance
to get to the top.
>> PROBST: The remaining members
of John's shattered alliance
fought with each other to stay
in the game.
>> From the get go, I didn't
like you.
>> PROBST: Sean and Paschal won
a Marquesan feast in the reward
challenge.
>> Felt like Julius Caesar, man.
>> PROBST: And they smuggled
some food back to share with the
rest of the tribe.
>> Thank you so much for
bringing food back.
That is so nice of you.
>> PROBST: Tammy won a crucial
immunity challenge.
>> Whoo! Yes, yes, yes!
>> PROBST: And Soliantu went to
Tribal Council, where Zoe was
voted out of the tribe.
Zoe, the tribe has spoken.
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( theme song playing )
>> Day 28.
>> Ain't got long, sweetheart.
>> I know.
11 days.
11 days to go, that's it.
>> It was cold last night.
>> It was freezing last night.
>> Good morning.
How you doing, Sean?
>> Can't sleep.
My mattress.
>> It's got some lumps.
It's lumpy.
Lumpy.
>> We're all one big family,
man, we spoon, we snuggle, but
it's strictly for keeping warm.
I mean the whole love tribe
aspect of this game has been a
fallacy to a certain point.
Let's call ourselves the love
tribe when this game is over,
like will you really call me?
Will I really call you?
I think there are certain people
who genuinely are affectionate
and feel family vibes.
But in the context of a game
where people are trying to
position themselves, can a love
tribe truly exist?
>> Don't you know it's your
birthday?
You're not supposed to be
working on your birthday.
>> Well, it is my birthday.
>> Is it true?
>> Yes, it is.
>> Oh, my God, are you 20?
Or 21.
>> Happy birthday, girlfriend.
Birthday girl!
>> Got to blow it out.
>> In celebration of V's
birthday, we cut open the last
two bananas and mango.
Made her a little candle and
sang to her this morning, 'cause
we knew that was going to be the
best meal of the day, so...
>> Thank you, guys, so much.
>> Happy birthday.
>> If I wasn't at home, you guys
are the next best thing to be
with.
>> That's very sweet.
>> V's birthday was pretty
subdued, but as much as I could,
I kept trying to make her feel a
little bit special, being that,
you know, she's not with her
husband and her family.
>> I feel like we're all like
used spark plugs, because I'm
telling you it's a very, very
difficult time for me food wise
and just from the energy
perspective.
>> We don't really have much
choice in our dinner, lunch and
breakfast menu is pretty much
troko, taro and definitely
coconut.
>> You know, we tried in the
beginning, everybody's been
out there, trying to catch
something.
And even though we talk about
it, I think our energy wanes as
the day goes on, and the odds of
us actually catching a fish are
unfortunately diminishing.
>> There are black tip baby
sharks right here, in our front
yard.
And I'm determined.
They swim right under my feet.
I'm going to see if I can whack
it because they come so close.
You can see their little black
fins popping out of the water.
They're right here.
But there's too much wave action
here to see them.
They're taunting us, it's crazy.
It would be great food.
>> You know what?
From today's reward challenge, I
would give anything if the
reward was food.
>> I never thought I could feel
the inside of my ribs, but I do.
>> Oh, I'd give anything if it
was Oreo cookies and have, like,
Twix or Snickers ice cream to
put on top of the Oreo cookie,
and just inhale.
>> All the food that we've been
dreaming about.
>> Snickers, s'mores.
>> Oh, big fudge brownie.
>> Big fudge brownie.
>> A hot skillet with caramel.
>> Oh, God!
Oh, that sounds so good!
>> I think the sugar food
fantasy is making things worse
for everybody.
They just sort of get people
lethargic on a raft, thinking
about it and talking about it
instead of getting up and taking
some action to find new food.
It's fun, but at the same time I
do think the diversion is wrong.
I don't think it's healthy.
So I'm going to try to do some
different things for food, and
also mentally it's just a
diversion.
It feels better than sitting
around talking about sweets.
>> V, I'm holding on to a
thread, baby.
threat.
What are you talking about?
>> Just my energy, I can't put
it into words.
I'm just trying to hold on.
>> We're just trying to conserve
energy.
It is a pull to get through the
day now.
This is without a doubt the
worst place I have ever been on
Earth.
And it's just a constant battle
of dirt, filth, heat, sand,
wind, insects.
Everything about it is nasty,
dirty, filthy-- it's just pure
hell.
>> See if my check came in.
>> Let's see.
A place mat.
>> "You're about to hit rock
bottom."
>> All right, let's show this to
everybody else.
>> Was there anything else in
there?
>> Let me see.
Yep.
Here.
Birthday wish, baby.
Come on, give me a birthday hug.
>> Oh, my brother.
Thank you so much.
>> I know how much this means to
be away from home and our family
on this day.
I just want to tell you happy
birthday, sister, I love you,
okay?
>> No one likes to be away from
home on their birthday, of
course not.
But at that point that was kind
of tough.
Because I really hadn't thought
too much about being away from
Leander on my birthday.
So it was a little special and a
little sad as well.
I miss him so much.
I can't wait to see him.
>> I know.
>> But we are here and we are
going to do this.
God is with us, each and every
day.
>> We've been blessed beyond our
means, okay.
We can head back and give it
100%.
We'll have a nice meal there.
>> That's right. We gotta
remember that.
>> Exactly.
>> You guys, we got some good
tree mail!
>> Very good.
>> Somebody may be getting a
nice hot shower.
>> Ready?
"Should we just give you
treasures, I wouldn't hold your
breath.
"You're about to hit rock bottom
if you're faster than the rest.
"The style of the rich and
famous, pampered like a king,
"hot showers, clean clothes,
great food.
That's what victory brings."
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> God, we have to dive again.
>> Yeah, we got to go down.
>> Down, and it's going to be
tough going underwater.
(indistinct chatter)
>> I can swim to save my life if
you give me a short distance,
but I don't really feel too
comfortable in a whole lot of
water.
>> The worst thing you can do is
be overanxious, like overzealous
or anxious.
You just got to be real calm.
>> Either way it's going to be
tough.
>> Oh, God, it's going to be
hard.
>> Well, hey, I'd like to win a
reward.
I'd like to win something.
I need something.
>> Look around, man, all of us
are on our last leg.
>> PROBST: Good morning, guys.
Today's reward challenge is an
island version of musical
chairs.
First round starts with all
seven of you.
Scattered along the bottom of
the ocean floor are six shells.
They're marked by yellow rocks
to make them more visible.
The seven of you are going to
dive down.
Who ever comes up without a
shell is eliminated.
Next round, six people dive down
for only five shells; we'll do
this until we have four tribe
members left.
Those four will compete then
in a final sprint from the dock
to the shore carrying a 40-pound
rock underwater.
First one to drop the rock at my
feet wins the reward.
This is what you're playing for.
(laughter)
My personal Visa.
Which I will loan you for one
night.
You'll take this Visa and you'll
book yourself a room on a luxury
cruise ship.
That cruise ship right out
there.
(horn blowing)
So you go on board, check in,
make your way to your room.
I imagine you'll want to take a
nice, long, hot shower with all
the amenities, and a fresh set
of clothes.
New clothes for the first time
in 28 days.
You'll then make your way to one
of the observation decks where
you will enjoy a full course
meal.
All right.
Take a spot, wait for my go.
There are six shells, first six
of you back with these shells
move onto the next round.
Survivors ready!
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Go!
>> PROBST: General and Paschal
got a shell.
Tammy's got one.
Kathy's got a shell.
There are still shells down
there guys, don't quit.
V, are you giving up?
>> I'm giving up.
>> PROBST: Okay. Sean, there's
the opportunity, baby.
Let go of that buoy, swim over,
find a shell and get it.
>> I know, I just have to catch
my breath.
I'm going to go there.
>> PROBST: Look at that.
Neleh's got a shell.
Find that little bit of extra
strength and grab it.
Sean may have one.
Look at that!
Sean got a shell!
Yes!
(cheering)
Nice job.
>> Way to go. Whoo!
>> PROBST: Now you just got to
do it again.
Moving on to the next round.
V, you can head back to the
beach.
This round we're looking for
five.
There are five shells.
Survivors ready!
Go!
General and Paschal got a shell.
Tammy's got one.
Kathy's got a shell.
Neleh's got a shell.
There it is.
We got all five.
Nice work.
Kathy, General, Neleh, Tammy,
Paschal, moving on.
Sean, when you get your breath,
you're swimming in.
Nice effort.
Here we go, guys.
First four back with shells move
on to the final round.
Survivors ready!
Go!
Get down there Neleh, go!
Kathy's got one.
Tammy's got one.
Paschal's got one.
General's got it.
That's it, Neleh.
Catch your breath.
Neleh is going to swim on back.
You four stay here.
Wait for my go.
First one to bring a yellow
stone back to me wins.
Survivors ready!
Go!
>> Come on, Pappy!
Bring it home!
>> Yeah, Pappy!
>> Come on, Pap!
>> PROBST: Paschal is pulling
away.
(cheering)
>> Come on, baby!
>> Come on, baby, come on now!
>> Come on, Pappy!
>> Bring it home!
>> Don't look back.
Don't look back.
You're doing great.
Come on, man.
>> Come on, Paps.
(all cheering Paschal on)
>> PROBST: Nice job.
Well earned.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Here's the deal.
I'll hold on to the Visa card,
we're going to bring the cruise
ship to you.
We'll get you a shower and some
food.
Guys, good effort, everybody out
there.
>> Wow, Pappy, your own cruise
ship.
There it is!
Oh, Pap, way to go, baby.
>> Very cool.
>> All of a sudden there's this
cruise ship, and the closer the
ship got, the more excited I
got.
And I was ready to swim out to
it.
It's a beautiful sight.
All for me.
>> Don't cheat yourself on the
desserts, Pas, you know that.
>> You know what's really good,
bananas foster, because we're on
French Polynesia.
>> That's the thing to get?
>> That's a French dessert.
>> Just open up the menu and say
okay, bring it all on.
>> Paschal! Come on aboard.
>> Bye, guys!
>> Bye!
>> Bye, Pappy.
He's going to be in a warm
shower in no time.
>> PROBST: Okay, I got to tell
you.
I hate for you to have this
great experience all alone.
>> Okay,
>> PROBST: So, is there one
tribe member you want to bring?
>> You got to be kidding me.
>> PROBST: No.
>> Neleh!
(Neleh screams)
>> Oh, wow.
>> Have fun, Neleh!
>> There was no conscious
decision; it was automatic
spontaneous reaction.
She's just the epitome of a
young lady that deserves it.
It was a wonderful opportunity
to enjoy something together.
(Neleh shrieks)
>> You deserved it.
>> Did she deserve as much as
anybody else? I mean, to me, it
was V's birthday that day.
She was feeling a little down,
and I don't know, had I won I
would definitely have picked V.
(Neleh screaming)
>> Bye!
>> Oh, my God!
Oh, that is so sweet.
>> If I go home tomorrow, I will
be like the happiest woman in
the whole wide world.
We were just beside ourselves
with excitement.
I've never been on a cruise ship
before, and I had never thought
that it would be that beautiful.
>> Thank you.
Oh, it smells so good, Paschal.
Here, Pappy and I, we're
these grubby little rugrats
coming on to this really, really
nice cruise ship.
It was just awesome.
>> PROBST: Here's the deal, my
Visa card.
Michelle's going to check you
in.
Enjoy your night.
>> We appreciate it.
>> PROBST: Okay.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Bye, guys.
>> Bye, bye, Jeff.
Thanks.
Hello, how you doing?
>> Good.
>> This is really something.
This is beautiful.
>> This is your room key.
Welcome aboard.
>> Thank you so much.
We're going to take you to your
room.
>> Oh, wow!
>> Oh, look at this.
>> Oh, my heavens.
Paschal, there's candy right
away!
Our clothes-- we haven't had
forever!
>> Look at the view!
Oh, How cool is this! I mean
look at this!
This is our own boat.
The ship was just absolutely
beautiful.
I can imagine how the royalties
of people on Earth must live,
because that's what we were
presented with.
>> Oh, my gosh, Paschal, look at
yourself in the mirror.
>> Oh, no!
>> It was just so weird to see
myself for the first time.
My hair looked like it was dark
brown, just greasy dread locks.
It was just gross.
It just felt so refreshing to
have hot water just pouring down
your body.
I mean, this was like luxury.
I put my hair up in this nice
fluffy white towel, put lotion
all over.
>> Whoo! Gosh!
That was wonderful!
I haven't felt this good in over
a month.
>> I felt like a whole new
person.
I didn't even feel like I was in
the game anymore, to tell you
the truth.
This is a dream come true,
Paschal.
We are so lucky to be here.
I'm so lucky to be here with
you.
>> Oh, look at this.
>> Oh, my heck!
Oh, cool.
We went around the corner and
there's this one table set up,
with the white linen cloth, like
ten pieces of silverware.
>> Cheers, darling, my little
daughter.
>> Cheers, Pappy.
>> Oh, look what's coming.
>> Don't even.
Oh, my gosh, it's bread!
>> Thanks.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my heck.
>> The best bread I've ever had.
>> The best butter I've ever
had.
>> To see them go off onto that
boat and we came back here to
prepare our muscley troko
shells.
That was a tough one.
None of us was happy.
>> Neleh is probably ordering
desert first.
And then again desserts.
>> Neleh's hair is probably
nicely conditioned and
shampooed, and it's probably
just flowing so nicely right
now.
>> I bet you she got it blow
dried.
>> Just beautiful, and having a
really good time.
>> You guys think they'll be
able to smuggle any food back?
>> Yeah.
>> So the next thing that came
out was, oh, what's it called,
what's the delicacy?
>>Escargot, that's for you, sir.
>> Thank you so much.
I don't think I've ever
had escargot.
I knew what escargot was, but I
couldn't envision that snail
would taste good.
>> Wow.
>> Oh.
>> Yum!
>> Oh, my heck.
Cream potatoes, vegetables.
>> Would you care to have some
wine?
>> I wouldn't care for any.
>> I wouldn't either.
>> Thank you.
>> I just hope they don't get
upset and vote me out because of
this.
>> Paschal!
>> Dessert was the final course
and it was creme brulee which
I've never eaten in my life.
>> Ooh, what is that?
>> It is so sugary.
Man, that was good.
I was really looking forward to
the bill because I had no idea
what something like this would
cost, I figured maybe $150.
>> Holy cow!
Oh, my heck!
>> The bill was $312.
Which of course I didn't flinch
because it was not my money.
It could have been $3,000 and it
wouldn't have mattered to me.
Tip.
That's $200.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Worth every penny of it.
Thank you very much.
>> Thank you, sir.
Have a nice evening.
>> Thank you.
>> $200 tip.
>> Paschal, I can't laugh
anymore.
I'm going to puke.
>> They're going to have beer
breath.
>> Neleh doesn't drink and
neither does Paschal.
They got the wrong people on
board to do some drinking.
>> Boy, that's for sure.
>> I would have been throwing
them back.
>> We were all sitting on the
raft waiting for them to come
back.
Everybody sitting there
wondering, do you think they're
going to bring food back?
Do you think they're going to
bring food?
>> Hi!
>> Hi. Did you have a great
time?
>> Oh, wow.
>> Look at your blow-dried hair.
>> We had the best time.
>> Don't get near me, I smell.
>> Hi, guys!
>> Oh, I'm going to puke if I
get too close.
>> Hi, guys.
>> Look how cleaned up you guys
are.
>> The first thing I did was I
stuck my face in Neleh's hair,
and her hair just smelled
fantastic.
>> There's a bathroom off to the
right and they had, you know,
the shampoo and the like a
loofah sponge.
I had to take the loofah sponge
and literally scrub.
It's almost like when you peel
stuff off your body, it's like
that black flaky stuff.
>> She was going on a little too
much about her shower and how
clean she was.
She's so damn sweet.
>> Anyway, and so the first
thing they brought out was a big
basket of bread.
And then after that...
>> The food sounded really good.
It kind of sucked listening to
them describe it in detail.
>> I wish so bad I could have
brought something back, you
guys.
I feel horrible telling you guys
about this.
Did you guys feel horrible
telling us?
>> No, but then we also brought
back some food.
>> The only thing I have left to
share is this mint that I shoved
in my mouth really fast.
So if everybody wants to take a
little nibble.
>> I'm okay, sweetheart.
>> Come on, you guys.
It's good, it's a little hard
mint; I don't want it.
>> You're offering seven
starving adults a piece of candy
out of your mouth.
Keep your mint candy, man.
You know, that's like saying
anybody want this piece of doo-
doo.
>> Nobody wants this?
>> Morning, guys.
>> Good morning.
>> Look how clean you are.
>> Oh, man.
I had the best night's sleep
ever.
>> The next morning when we wake
up, Neleh is still on the clean
kick, just kind of being the
princess.
And has her feet propped up in
her new clean clothes, looking
at her nails.
>> Can't believe my skin is
clean.
>> This is so weird.
>> Who cares if your nails are
clean or dirty?
I mean, there's chores to be
done and there's regular living
back on Soliantu.
She's one of those people who
cleverly will have the
perception that she's working,
but I don't really see her
carrying jugs.
I don't see her lifting wood, I
don't really see her doing the
work that she says she's doing.
But she's always the first one
to go, "I have so much energy."
I'm like I would too, if I
wasn't doing anything but taking
naps and walking and relaxing.
>> How is your porridge coming,
Kath?
>> Well, let me see the
ingredients.
>> I think it's going to taste
just like it did the other day.
>> Yuck.
>> Do you want porridge or do we
want flank steak?
(Paschal chuckling)
>> I hear you, Pappy.
>> You do?
>> I think Neleh has definitely
snowed Paschal and everyone
else.
I think she's playing this game
harder than anybody left on this
island, and she's playing sweet
little girl next-door, and
before you know it, hey, I'm in
the finals and I'm so happy, and
oh, God, this is, oh heck.
>> And the bread, then you dip
it...
>> Hey, Neleh, you want to get
green leaves for our taro?
>> Absolutely.
Porridge hot, porridge cold.
>> I think Neleh has about 60 to
70% sweetness and about 30% or
40% she's working it.
I think it's a little much right
now, and she's working it too
hard.
She genuinely cares for everyone
here, but I think she's working
it with Paschal.
She's hovering under his wings
for protection.
>> Paschal, do you want any
taro?
>> No thank you, not right now.
>> Where is that creme brulee?
>> Hey, big man, come here and
sit in the shade.
>> I just had a little coconut,
and now I'm ready to do pig
snare.
Who wants to help?
>> A pig snare?
>> Sure.
He comes out here every night,
and he's about this tall.
I got a good look at him.
So I got a pig that comes down
into our camp every night.
I'm getting a little tired of
him taunting me, so I want to go
and catch that thing and make
some pork chops.
I figured this one, we bend it
over that way.
That way we won't really have to
bend it that far, but when he
lashes it, he'll be up.
>> Rob is building a pig snare.
I think because not only he's a
little bit frustrated that we
haven't got a pig, but I think
Rob wants to secure his place in
the tribe.
If he doesn't win, you know, the
next immunity challenge or the
following immunity challenge, at
least if he wins a pig, he can
hold that up and say, "Hey, I'm
a valuable member of this tribe.
Don't vote me out."
>> It might hold if this one was
farther down.
>> Whoa, it's all right.
I got it.
>> I catch a pig tonight, you
win immunity, and I'm going to
tell them, look, she's immune, I
caught the pig.
You can't get rid of me and not
let me have any of my pig, you
got to keep me, I got a pig.
And then he'll pull, look at
that release.
>> Guys, we got mail!
>> Mail, at this hour, weird.
>> Sounds like it's happening
tonight.
>> Happening tonight?
>> Big wow.
All right, guys, ready?
>> Yeah.
>> "Race against the others
until you're feeling hot.
"The most basic skill of
survival, show them what you've
got.
"Food, water and protection,
most important in this game.
"You may as well just pack your
bags if you fail to strike
flame."
>> Guess what we're doing
tonight.
We're going to have to make fire
>> We've got to make fire.
>> That's what it sounds like.
>> Yeah, we've got to make fire.
Yet another curve ball.
I've been busting my butt all
day, you know, chopping wood,
making a new pig snare and
everything like that.
These other people have been
sleeping all day and resting.
I wish I knew that.
You know, I thought it was a day
off.
It's big stakes for me.
I think I don't win, I could go.
>> PROBST: Welcome guys to
Tribal Beach.
First things first.
Tammy, you want to give back
that immunity necklace.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity, up for
grabs.
Okay.
Here's the deal.
Tonight's game is especially
tough because it takes place in
the dark.
First, you're going to run to
the end of the course and gather
firewood from the perimeter.
You will build a fire under a
wok to heat oil to pop popcorn.
Once you've popped one kernel
of popcorn, you'll move to a
final station where you will
light your pyre from the bottom
to ignite the top.
You'll start your fire in a way
you haven't done yet.
Magnesium, flint and steel.
First person to ignite the top
of their pyre wins immunity,
cannot be voted out, guaranteed
three more days in this game.
Everything clear?
Take your spots.
Wait for my go.
Survivors ready!
Go!
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: Think about stuff
that's really going to ignite.
Coconut husks work really well.
There you go, V.
V has fire.
General's got fire.
V and the General have fire.
Everybody else is still working.
That a way Sean.
Keep it going.
Kathy's got fire.
Sean's got fire.
>> You don't got any matches, do
you, Jeff?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Neleh's got fire.
>> Whoo!
How close are we to having
popcorn?
Very close, look at that oil,
really heating up.
Let's go, General, get one
kernel to pop and you're moving
on.
>> I hear sizzle, man, I hear
sizzle.
Look at that, look at that.
Look at that.
It popped, right there.
>> PROBST: General, you got
popcorn, baby.
Moving on to the third station,
you're done here.
General's in the lead.
It's getting close.
Wok's heating up.
There it is.
V's got popcorn, moving to the
final station.
First one to ignite the top wins
immunity.
General's got a good healthy
fire going, V.
You'd better get that fire going
fast.
General's looking good, very
close.
Very close, General.
V's catching up.
They're neck and neck, guys.
>> Come on, baby. Yeah!
You're close, baby.
>> PROBST: General.
Yeah! Nice work.
Immunity, brother. Turn around
here and let me put this on.
>> Sanctuary.
>> PROBST: You cannot be voted
out. Congratulations.
>> You ain't going nowhere.
I'm going to try my damnedest.
(laughter)
>> How tall do you think this
is, you guys?
Probably about 250 feet, maybe
higher.
>> No, about 100 feet.
>> 100 feet?
>> Just won immunity, feeling a
little relieved, knowing I'm
definitely going to be here
another three days.
>> Who else gets this?
>> It's like being in a
torrential downpour and it's
gorgeous.
>> The win was very big for me,
just lifted me up and bringing
me back to life.
I was feeling a little down, and
now I'm feeling really good
about myself again.
That was refreshing.
I'm definitely a little bummed
that it looks like Tammy is on
the way out.
She's like a sister to me.
I'd like to see if I could do
something to save her.
>> I think Tammy has a play for
tonight.
I just don't know what it is.
I think it's something that's
going to get pulled out of a hat
and we're all going to come
tumbling down.
All right.
>> Over.
>> Hike, hike!
>> Over, hike, hike!
>> I'm not used to losing.
I'm super competitive.
And you know what?
I'm not giving up on this game
until I hear my name read at
Tribal Council.
>> I'm telling you something.
That Tammy is waiting for any
opening.
>> Oh, Tammy's waiting for
anything.
She's like a pit bull.
>> She's waiting there to take
advantage of something.
>> That's why I'm saying, you
know, if she comes up with some
plan, I can see her getting V
over on her side.
>> V has definitely flipped more
than anybody in this game.
Maybe Rob and Tammy could
somehow convince Sean and V
to join their pact.
>> A few moments we get to have.
If V and I hooked up with Tammy
and Rob, point blank, it would
put us in the final four.
My thing is, I'm approaching you
on this angle.
Neleh got mad game.
She's playing the girl next-door
role to the hilt.
It's important that V and I vote
Neleh off.
Because she's so young and
because she has this angelic
girl-next-door, everybody is
being deceived by aww, aww, and
not realizing the more sympathy
you have, the stronger this girl
gets.
She talks a good game, let's go
do this, let's go do this, but
don't do much but sleep and take
walks.
>> Every now and then she'll
turn around and pick up
something and make it look
like...
>> See, you see exactly what I'm
saying.
>> It would be a sure bet if V
and I hooked up with Tammy and
Rob, but then again, it might
not be a sure bet, because they
may very well go to the other
force, and say hey, look, these
two tried to hook up with us and
save their own ass.
Then we're on the chopping
block.
>> I'm ready to end this game in
a bang, baby.
We are close.
All right.
So we'll see what happens.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: I will now bring in
the two members of our jury.
I'll remind you the jury is here
merely to observe.
This is the beginning of the
shift in the game, when the
power leaves those who are still
in it and goes now to those who
are out of it.
So how you vote becomes very
important in this game.
Tonight I want to talk about
what you are tired of, after 30
days.
Neleh.
>> A big part of it is that you
are covered in dirt.
You know, you wake up in the
morning, there's dirt and no-nos
stuck inside your eyes.
It's just, it's absolutely
disgusting, and I mean the
nights are bad here.
>> PROBST: Kathy?
>> I can't stay on the beach.
For various reasons, it's the
bugs, the monotony, it's the
grime.
And my skin is literally ready
to fall off, I've got so many
rashes and infections, it's
disgusting.
>> PROBST: Paschal, what are you
sick of out here?
>> Just the daily grinds, the
monotony, the same food, the
same living conditions, the same
everything.
And the closer we get to the
end, it seems the more
difficult it becomes.
>> PROBST: On a scale of one to
ten, how valuable was the reward
of going to a cruise ship and
being able to take a shower and
get clean clothes and have a
good meal?
>> Seven million.
Neleh and I sat on the deck of
that ship and talked about it.
There was nothing, nothing that
I could have received that would
have invigorated me more and
made me feel better.
It was absolutely amazing.
>> PROBST: Kathy, what was your
reaction?
Paschal and Neleh come back, not
only did they have a shower,
they're clipping their nails,.
They're doing a little buff pad,
I mean it was like they went to
a spa.
>> Hey, there is no doubt about
it, I was jealous.
I think all of us had a
difficult time listening to the
blow by blow description of
Neleh's shower.
But Paschal did an incredible
job on that challenge, man, so I
think when you win, you deserve
it.
And Neleh going, so be it.
But I wanted to get him really
dirty the next day.
>> PROBST: General, you own
immunity.
If it made sense, you could
assign that immunity to somebody
else.
Have you talked about that, is
there somebody here you want to
give that up to?
Do you feel safe enough?
>> No, I got to stay.
>> PROBST: It's time to vote.
Neleh, you're first.
>> Tammy, you're one cool chick
but lethal competition.
Take it easy.
>> You don't seem to pull your
weight actually as much as
everybody else pulls theirs.
So that's why I'm voting for you
tonight.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person will be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Tammy.
Vecepia.
Two votes Tammy, two votes V.
That's three votes Tammy.
Tammy.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Tammy, the tribe has spoken.
Well, you made it 30 days; I
know you're having a hard time,
but nobody ever said Survivor
was going to be easy.
Nine more days left.
Hang in there.
You guys can head back to camp.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: Only six remain at
Soliantu, and island life has
taken its toll on all of them.
>> We're just depleted energy
wise, and it's really uncanny to
see what's happening with our
mental stability.
>> PROBST: And an event occurs
that will shakeup the entire
tribe.
>> It takes an experience like
this to realize what really is
important in your life.
>> Even though I knew tonight
was coming, and it was my turn,
it still sucks to be voted off.
I've played this game exactly
the way I said I was going to
play it and I'm proud of the way
I played it.
This is the game of Survivor,
the people that are left, I hope
that they have it in them to
last the rest of the time,
because I'm not so sure they do.