>> PROBST: We're on board the
fishing trawler Amaryllis,
making our way through the very
rough waters of the South
Pacific.
Down below, deep inside the hold
of this ship, 16 Americans,
about to be abandoned in the
middle of the Marquesas, part of
Tahiti's mystical islands.
Thousands of miles from the
nearest continent, this will be
their home for the next 39 days.
But this time the game is
different.
These survivors will be given no
food, absolutely no rations.
Each tribe will leave the ship
with only the barest of
essentials: two machetes, two
cooking pots, two empty water
containers, one frying pan, one
filet knife, and one magnifying
glass.
They'll be left to fend for
themselves using the resources
of the land and their own
survival skills.
It is the ultimate challenge:
16 strangers forced to work
together to create a new society
while battling the elements and
each other.
They must learn to adapt or
they'll be voted out of the
tribe.
In the end, only one will remain
to claim the million-dollar
prize.
39 days, 16 people...
one survivor.
>> PROBST: As this ship drops
anchor, these 16 Americans began
the adventure of a lifetime.
They have never spoken to each
other, and have been divided
into the two competing tribes:
Maraamu and Rotu, Tahitian words
for "wind" and "rain."
Each tribe will be given a crate
which holds a minimal amount of
supplies, but no food and no
water.
They then face a difficult two-
mile paddle to their beaches and
their new homes for the next 39
days.
( shouting )
>> Okay!
>> Woo!
>> Let's get away from the boat.
>> Over here.
>> PROBST: The Rotu Tribe, which
will always wear blue, consists
of Kathy Vavrick-O'Brien, a real
estate agent from Burlington,
Vermont;
Gabriel Cade, a bartender from
Celo, North Carolina;
Tammy Leitner, a crime reporter
from Mesa, Arizona;
Paschal English, a judge from
Thomaston, Georgia;
John Carroll, a registered nurse
from Omaha, Nebraska;
Neleh Dennis, a student from
Layton, Utah.
Zoe Zanidakis, a fishing boat
captain from Monhegan Island,
Maine;
and Robert DeCanio, a limousine
driver from Queens, New York.
The Maraamu Tribe, which will
always wear yellow, consists of
Gina Crews, a nature guide from
Gainesville, Florida;
Sean Rector, a teacher from
Harlem, New York;
Sarah Jones, an account manager
from Newport Beach, California;
Rob Mariano, a construction
worker from Canton,
Massachusetts;
Vecepia Towery, an office
manager from Portland, Oregon;
Peter Harkey, a bowling alley
owner from Millis,
Massachusetts;
Patricia Jackson, a truck
assembler from Lugoff,
South Carolina;
and Hunter Ellis, a Federal
Express pilot from La Jolla,
California.
>> One, two, three, four, five.
>> Guess what.
We haven't moved at all in,
like, the last half hour.
>> We were making zero progress.
I don't know how long we were
out there, but every one of us
were totally exhausted.
>> I think we're going exactly
.2 miles per hour.
>> Okay, don't stop rowing!
>> One...
two...
three...
four.
Over to that cliff.
>> Really well, excellent work.
>> Rotu, Rotu.
Rotu, Rotu.
>> We were singing and trying to
get some sort of rowing motion,
you know, like on an old whaler
there.
And it really brought us
together.
>> ...three... four...
five... six... seven...
>> We're getting there.
>> ...six, seven, eight.
Woo!
We made it!
Can you believe it?
>> My first thought when we hit
the beach was, "Thank you, God,
for letting us hit this beach."
I was just happy to have made
it.
>> Everybody was so psyched.
They were just running around
and congratulating each other
and we were thrilled.
We made it.
We made it the first part of
the way.
>> Wonderful to be here, guys.
>> So our tribe is Rotu!
( cheering )
>> It was great when we rounded
that final corner.
You know, we had seen a lot of
coves, and we weren't sure if
this was the one.
We thought it was the one, and
then finally to see the flag
coming home-- it was great.
( cheering )
Wave the flag!
>> As we were coming in, last
maybe 50 yards or so, we all
made a concerted effort to give
a last heave to make it to land,
and it was quite evident that
Sarah wasn't doing anything at
all.
Stroke, stroke.
Kick, kick.
Kick.
Stroke, stroke.
>> Sarah's arrival was almost
like Cleopatra.
It was like the servants are
paddling and lifting and she's
sitting on a crate looking so
marvelous with her boobs hanging
out and her Goldilocks in the
air.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Save it, you know?
This is Survivor.
Nobody trying to look at you
like that here.
>> Home sweet home.
>> Yes!
>> When we first arrived on
land, I can't even describe it.
It was beyond words.
First of all, I had never been
on an ocean, ever.
I mean, in the hood, ain't a lot
of pools, you know, probably
don't really swim too much.
>> How you doing, man?
Are you going to make it?
>> It's emotional when I think
about the miracles that God has
performed for me.
We didn't do this on our own.
He definitely... his Hand was
under the raft guiding us.
God, we thank you.
We is in the ocean.
And you led us here, God.
>> Sean and Peter immediately
bonded.
They went into the water and
they had their prayer Baptism
revival.
>> We can do all things through
Christ.
>> This told me that either Sean
and Peter were either really
playing the game starting real
early, or they were definitely
off their rockers.
>> All these things, we pray,
for your son, Jesus Christ,
Amen.
>> You guys ready to look in the
box?
>> Let's go do the box!
>> Yeah!
>> Woo! We got it!
>> Oh, it's not as much as we
thought!
>> Our crate had no food.
No food at all.
>> I had no idea that this would
be like this out here.
But I mean, we're here.
We know we have to survive and
it's tough, so we just do
whatever we can.
>> Hey, hey, what's this?
>> Hey, hey, hey.
>> All right, what's this?
>> Must be a map.
A water map.
>> The stuff that was in the
crate-- we got a map to our
water spot.
We got, like, two pots and a
pan, two machetes and a small
knife, and then a magnifying
glass.
>> Woo!
>> Oh, my God.
>> Let's get going.
Let's build a fire.
>> All right, we need tinder.
>> We were soaking wet and we
had a limited amount of daylight
left, so our first thing was to
get fire.
>> Keep doing what you're doing.
Good job.
It's working.
>> We landed so late.
The sun was down;
the clouds were up.
>> Oh...
>> That's a lot of cloud, too.
>> I mean we tried and tried and
tried, and it just didn't work.
>> This is not going to work.
>> Okay.
>> And Kathy, she's like, "We
have to have fire and we have to
have it right now."
So we tried the "two pieces of
wood" method.
>> Yeah, yeah, man!
This is not going to work.
>> Okay.
>> Kathy slips very easily into
the role of the skipper.
Maybe it's her personality.
Maybe it's the difficulty of
being out here.
I don't know.
But we didn't need a skipper.
>> All right, well, let's just
rotate.
All right, I'll be right back.
>> We have been rotating.
>> Keep going. Come on.
Good.
Go, Johnny, go.
>> We were plowing, plowing,
plowing and after rolling for
all those hours, our arms were
just spent.
>> No.
>> So we didn't get fire the
first day, which sucked.
>> I definitely knew this game
was going to be hard when we got
here and there was no food.
There was nothing in the box.
>> What's in there?
We knew that if we didn't work
as a team, one of us was going
to starve to death.
>> What's in this?
>> That's a magnifying glass.
>> If that's a magnifying glass
we got about an hour to collect
some wood and start a fire.
>> Hunter's leadership role
started when we got here.
You know, immediately Hunter
said we needed to, you know,
stake out where we want to put
the fire.
>> Hey, you guys?
We got a magnifying glass, so if
we can collect a ton of
firewood, we have only got about
an hour and a half, two hours
left.
>> I'm already in love with
Hunter.
He's a great person.
We have so much in common.
Hunter knows a little bit about
everything.
>> I think the prevailing wind
is going to probably switch and
come from this direction.
>> "The prevailing wind"?
This is the weather station over
here?
>> I know you mean well, but you
sound like, "a little bit of
wind flowing to the east, but in
the morning when we wake up, the
sun will be up."
My nickname for Hunter is
MacGyver, simply because he got
way too much energy for me out
here.
>> You know what I was thinking?
If we can get some of the banana
leaves, and if it starts to
rain, we have the banana leaf
funnel.
>> You can drink rainwater,
right?
>> Out here he's going to turn
into MacGyver.
Everybody, let's make a funnel
out of a banana plant so in the
morning we can get the
nutrients, because the winds
will be blowing to the east.
>> I see that Hunter is starting
to be a focal point where
everybody is going to check with
him first.
I'm a alpha male, too, so I find
it hard to just follow somebody
just blindly and keep going like
they're my daddy.
I'm not going to do that.
They better know, I'm from
Harlem and I'm representing.
>> We got 40 minutes and that
sun is behind the mountain.
>> Sometimes the angle, the tilt
of the lens.
Tilt it a little bit.
Okay.
That's a good one.
>> So I mean, it's so close.
I tried my best for 15 minutes
and actually, we got some smoke.
We got some good smoke.
We just couldn't get it
completely going.
>> The problem in lighting the
fire is having maintain an air
flow to keep it going.
>> Peter, we need you over here.
>> We got to have someone
blowing.
People know that I'm into yoga.
You know, I did that about ten
years ago, and in yoga, you
breathe from the diaphragm, so I
was able to take nice, long,
deep breaths.
( blowing )
>> Yeah!
>> Come on.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Yoga definitely helps with
lighting the fire.
>> We got fire!
>> Here we go.
>> Keep the fuel up.
Keep the fuel up.
Don't let it go out.
>> Let's not let it go out.
>> Robert rocks!
( chattering )
>> I want a monkey if I win any
amount of money.
I want a monkey.
You want a monkey too?
>> Yeah.
You want a little curious
George?
>> Sarah has a very cute body.
She paid a lot for it.
And if you have it, of course
flaunt it.
I do not think that Sarah is
using her body to get through
this game, but I do think that
if she connects with the right
individual, then that will
definitely help her get through.
>> I want to go look at the bed.
I didn't get to check it out.
>> Who is going to sleep inside
this?
>> I don't got my shoes on.
>> Right on top of it.
>> I thought we were going to
sleep in there.
Is it comfy?
>> Oh, yeah, it's like a
waterbed.
>> Oh!
>> You all right?
>> Oh, dude, I can go to sleep
right now.
>> Last night there was
definitely flirtation around Rob
and Sarah.
>> We fill this thing up and let
it cook in the sun all day
tomorrow...
>> There you go.
>> We got a hot tub.
>> That's an idea.
>> Yeah, or just a little
swimming pool, or whatever.
>> Get some cocktails, too.
You'll figure out a way.
>> When we got into the raft
that we had paddled in on and
they kind of just hung out away
from everybody else, and were
there pretty much the whole darn
night.
So at that point in time, that
was another question" what are
they saying, you know?
Are they flirting or are they
making an alliance?
And you shouldn't put yourself
in that situation if you don't
want people to think that.
>> Anybody have any water?
>> Are these all empty?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> That's five.
>> When we first landed on the
island we knew we were going to
run out of water in a hurry.
We each had one coconut full of
water, which is about a liter,
and you really need a gallon a
day.
>> Well, if we follow the river
up we get to a little stream
there.
>> That's a good idea.
>> ( whistles )
Hey, you guys!
This is the way.
I found the way.
I did not want to go into this
being the blond bitchy person at
all 'cause I'm really not.
The only time I do get assertive
is when I see that a critical
job isn't getting done.
Is that primeval or what?
It's incredible.
>> There's a waterfall!
>> Are you kidding me?
Woo!
Start swimming, baby.
>> Go, go, go.
>> We were so excited when we
found that waterfall, like, I
saw it for the first time and I
could not believe my eyes.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Woo!
>> Come on, guys!
>> I was like, this is awesome!
>> You tell me there's not a
god.
>> I don't want to go home.
>> That waterfall was just, ah,
it was like sanctuary.
Damn, I think it's taro.
We found a ton of taro, so we
got food; we got water.
These surroundings will give you
everything, so you've gotta be
close to Mother Earth now.
If you never were before, now's
the time.
>> Now that we found this
waterfall, it's dynamite, and
then it's just the fire, that
damn fire.
So I'm just going to work on the
fire when we get back.
I'm going to work on it until
it's dark.
>> Stop.
>> Oh, there it goes.
Oh, sweet!
>> This is grapefruit, right?
It smells like grapefruit.
When we open it up we can tell
because we'll know what it looks
like.
>> Everybody, a toast.
Cheers!
To Maraamu.
>> Maraamu!
>> When I first arrived here I
realized that we had no food at
all, and I didn't want to be
eating lemons and grapefruits
the entire time we're here.
( rooster crowing )
Did you hear that?
Listen, can you hear that
gobbling?
Sounds like a turkey.
Do you hear it?
I'm being dead serious.
I don't know if chickens make
that sound too.
So I decided that I would try to
get some meat for us.
There are chickens and pigs in
this area.
Yo, yo, yo, don't move.
There's a chicken.
I swear to God.
He's got to come down, right?
He's right up there.
>> That thing is huge!
>> Dude, that is dinner right
there.
Come on, we've got to get him
down.
I'll grab him and just snap him.
Roosters can't fly, can they?
>> I had no idea that roosters
can fly.
But this rooster took off like a
747.
He was out of there.
And that was it.
>> Did you get him?
Come on, chicken man.
Did you get him?
>> No.
I know.
I will.
>> At times Rob is a little
preoccupied with things that
don't really pertain to the
survival needs of the moment.
He wants to chase chickens, I
mean, I don't even think he
knows how to clean a chicken.
>> Maybe I don't have as much
experience as you guys do with
what needs to be done.
>> That's why I was getting a
little frustrated because if we
collect a lot of firewood, if we
get the water going, if we
finish the shelter, once we've
got all those things, then we do
the luxury items.
>> Hunter felt that I was
spending too much time trying to
hunt down meat and I needed to
be around helping with the daily
chores.
One down.
I realized that I'm going to
have to work hard...
Two down.
...to stay in the group now, and
that this is essentially going
to be my fate.
>> It's so important to get
fire.
This is the most important thing
right now, so we need to get
a...
>> But yesterday...
>> We spent how many hours with
that thing yesterday?
I'm wiped.
>> How many hours did we spend
yesterday?
>> You tell me.
>> Not many, I don't think we
spend more than two.
>> Of course we know we have to
get fire.
But to have somebody, you know,
"The sky is falling!
The sky is falling!," it really
started to become grating.
>> I am not trying to be pushy
here.
>> No, no, no, I'm not saying
you are.
>> Okay, but our problem is
huge.
>> I'm saying right now I can't
do that.
>> Right, I'm not asking you to
do it.
>> You are asking.
You're saying "It's imperative.
We've got to get dynamic,
blah, blah, blah."
I'm just telling you I'm really
tired.
>> I'm not asking you to do it.
>> This isn't going to solve
anything here.
>> I don't have any support
here.
And I'm frustrated that these
people are being more cautious
about this.
>> I just don't like the
urgency.
You know, it's like, I'm working
my butt off and just getting all
panicky and stuff is
frustrating.
>> I'm Irish so I have that
Irish temper and she sparked it
and I did feel bad about it.
So then now I became fixated on
getting the fire to basically
neutralize my outburst.
So I was like, "Damn it.
I'm starting a fire."
>> Oh, sweet, sweet, sweet!
>> Oh, we're not even getting
full sun.
You're going to get full sun in
a second.
Keep it going.
You're going to get a big old
blast.
>> Oh, wow, there we go, baby.
Here, sun, sun, sun.
>> Nice.
Yeah!
>> Thank you!
>> Yes!
>> Fire!
>> Yeah!
>> You knew if you left those
kids alone for a few minutes,
we could do something right.
>> Once we had the fire, then
everything was forgotten, and
she really started to come
around with a personality, and
attempting to bond.
>> We got fire, girlfriend.
I know it was important with
you.
>> Kathy.
No, no.
You put the fire under my butt,
you take it.
>> The nectar of gods.
>> I think it's those two
coconut trees right there.
See?
Large boulder.
>> That's where we have to get
the water from.
>> Water, I wonder if we can go
up this giant creek?
We're going to go hike up to the
water source.
Go check it out.
>> We got a little bit of an
adventure, but the big thing is
we need to get the water so we
can start tackling all the other
things without getting
dehydrated.
>> Do you think we go up more?
>> No, no, this is it.
We done looked.
This is it.
>> All right!
Agua.
And it bubbled up.
This is the beginning of it.
See it bubbling over there?
>> Oh, that looks nice.
>> Oh, yeah, we got water.
Where's the other one?
Mountain spring.
Here.
>> It was a huge relief that
there was actually water there
because it's the dry season now,
so we were excited, got our
water, came back to the fire and
immediately started boiling.
>> I'm a workaholic anyhow.
I caught myself trying to do too
much.
You know, everyone is trying to
put their best face forward and
trying to show that they're an
integral part of the team, and
all of a sudden I realized that
I had to just, like, slow down.
Then I went over and talked to
Sean.
Sean was great, you know.
He's telling me to chill.
>> Man, this feels so good.
>> Are you chilling all?
>> Under the shade, something
with some support.
We're chilling.
Right?
Isn't that what we're doing?
>> We're chilling.
You got to tell me some Harlem
stuff.
I want to go back and...
>> Harlem stuff?
That's not Harlem stuff, man.
Well, give me some stuff to work
with, for God's sakes!
>> Where you going to use it?
Where you going to use, uh...
You going to walk up to a
brother and go "Hey, I'm
chilling."
>> We talked and he almost, for
me, reminded me simply of, you
know, and it's really
comfortable to be yourself.
Then all of a sudden different
tribe members came over and like
we were having a real
conversation.
And it's nice to have real
conversation with people.
If someone said...
all this la-di-da and it's
simply to master every hole in
your body, how you breathe, how
you speak, how you see, how you
hear, how you urinate, how you
go to the bathroom and until you
are aware of even that, most
people around aren't even aware
they have seven holes in their
head.
>> He looks like a normal guy,
you know, but he's going on and
on about being holy.
And I'm thinking he's talking
about spiritualness, but he's
talking about actual holes in
your body.
I mean, he's a Froot Loop.
>> The holes of your
elimination, people don't like
to talk about it, but, it's
really, I mean, if you want to
be holy, you might as well start
with becoming aware.
>> Of your holes.
Holy.
>> All right, I've had enough of
this conversation.
>> Then you're aware of what
you're saying to people.
>> I don't understand what
you're talking about, not one
thing.
All of a sudden I loosen up, you
know, be yourself.
Sean did it to me.
I'm chilling here.
>> Ho, ho, ho!
Oh, my, our first mail.
>> We got mail!
>> Should we all open it
together?
>> Yeah, here we go.
Ooh!
What is it?
It's a message on a...
>> Oh, crap, we're going to have
to row some more.
>> Oh, no!
On the water?
>> All right.
Ready?
Read it out loud.
>> "You'll be in over your head
to get to the flame.
The weak ones will dread the
thought of this game.
It's a long tough trail.
Avoid a rocky start.
Fail to work as a team,
you'll be the first to part.
>> Ooh.
>> PROBST: Welcome.
How was the journey over, Sean?
>> Ha, y'all are crazy.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Anybody have any luck
with fire?
>> Yeah!
( applause )
>> PROBST: Good, because in
addition to no food, no water,
you're getting no fire help from
us at all of any kind at any
time.
That means if you have fire,
treasure it, take care of it.
When it rains, you better have a
backup plan.
There's no matches coming.
This is what you want to covet.
Everybody, put your hand on
that.
Everybody, get a little hand on
this immunity idol.
>> Yeah!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: It is your first
immunity challenge.
Win it, your tribe is guaranteed
another three days on the
island.
Lose, your tribe is going right
there, Tribal Council, somebody
is going to be the first person
voted out.
That brings us to today's
challenge.
Here's how it works.
Each tribe has an outrigger
canoe outfitted with two
torches, so you're looking at
about 300 pounds right now dry.
On my "Go," you're going to take
your canoe, run down the beach
and then swim with it out in the
ocean to the center wok, where
you will light both of your
torches.
Treasure those torches.
They're very important because
you're going to turn around and
start lighting your woks--
four-- as you make your way back
toward the beach.
Once you get to the beach, it's
a sprint down a very uneven and
very rocky beach where you will
light three more torches.
First tribe to reach the end,
get their canoe back in the
stand, and then light the final
wok, wins immunity.
You guys ready for this?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Get ready to start.
Wait for my "Go."
This is for immunity.
Survivors ready!
Go!
( shouting )
>> High, high, high, high, high.
Up, up.
( shouting )
>> We got somebody down.
>> Please do not tip the boat!
If this gets water in it, we are
screwed.
Light it up there.
Light it again!
Hurry.
>> Hurry up, hurry up!
♪ ♪
>> Woo!
>> Put the torch back.
>> No need, no need.
>> They're going to be coming
through the same way.
>> Someone get the last one.
( shouting indistinctly )
>> Woo!
>> PROBST: Rotu, immunity.
Who wants it?
You guys are safe for three more
days.
Unfortunately, one of you guys
are going home tomorrow night.
We have a day till Tribal
Council.
Good effort.
Head back that way.
I'll see you tomorrow.
One, two, three, Rotu!
>> We lost our first immunity
challenge yesterday, and today
we have to go to Tribal Council.
So the game has begun.
>> The party is over.
We first got here.
We started the fire early.
Everybody got to work.
But now we lost the challenge
and the reality set in.
Somebody has to go.
>> My strategy is to keep as
strong as, as strong as
possible.
>> The impression the tribe gave
me was that I needed to be voted
off to keep the tribe strong.
I'm not weak.
I know I'm not 25.
I'm twice that.
I know I can't keep up with you
in a foot race, but I can be
steady, I can endure, you know.
I said is it because I'm a woman
or I'm overweight, is it because
they think me a mama figure--
all that was going through my
mind.
>> A lot of times the person
that looks strongest right out
of the chute.
>> We don't know what's going to
happen, is all I'm saying.
>> That's called life.
>> I'm glad you told me your
strategy, but I don't want to
talk about it right now.
We're going to go tonight and
nobody is to convince me to vote
any way because I'm going to
vote the way I want to vote.
That's the way it is.
I guess Peter got on our nerves
this morning a little bit
because he came up and called us
all over and wanted to talk
about what the strategy of the
game was and how he was going to
do it.
>> I'm not this magical mystical
person, all right?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I think if you want to get
the truth of the situation, you
just can look in someone's eyes.
That's not just like, that's not
like, "Ooh!," you know.
I would have to say tonight that
I'm going to vote for Peter.
He's just got this strange smirk
on his face, always looks like
he's up to something.
He's just strange.
>> I know you don't have an
alliance.
I know I don't have an alliance.
>> I mean, an alliance right now
means absolutely nothing.
>> I did think about who I
possibly may want to vote out,
and I was thinking the whole
time maybe Sarah.
Just today feels too good to be
in the water and not, like,
doing stuff, you know?
>> When you look at Sarah and
you go, other than having two
floating devices that can help
us out there, what value is she
to the group, other than looking
cute?
It's very uncomfortable for all
of us because we're all one
family.
It's not chauvinistic, but the
more males you have in a camp,
the better I think you can
survive.
>> Good luck.
>> Good luck, Peter.
>> Thanks, bud.
>> There's three people that I
might choose to vote on:
Patricia, if you look at
physical strength, she is the
weakest person, maybe, just
because she's old;
Sarah, I think she knows she can
maybe use her body with the men,
the guys of the tribe;
and Peter because of what
happened this morning.
But right now I have no clue who
I'm going to vote for.
>> Eventually every one us is
going but the winner.
And who knows who that will be?
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
guys is a tribal torch.
Why don't you go ahead and find
your torch and approach the
flame?
Go ahead and put it back in its
slot.
We do this because fire does
represent life at Tribal
Council.
As long as you have fire, you
have life in this game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
It's that simple.
Now, all over the Marquesas
there are ancient dwellings like
this one, thousands of years
things have taken place,
everything from sacrifices to
other rituals.
Tribal Council is certainly a
ritual.
The vote, definitely a
sacrifice.
Because this is where you're
held accountable for your
actions on the island.
Sometimes those actions are
going to help you; sometimes
they're going to hurt you.
That's what the vote is all
about.
That's what we're going
to find out tonight.
But before we get to the first
vote, let's talk about the first
few days.
Gina, what's it like having to
source your own food, your own
water and your own fire?
Is it rewarding at the end of
the day to say, "We created all
of this?"
>> Yeah, it's very rewarding to
do that.
We're not given rice.
We're not given water.
We're not given fire.
We won't be given any of those
and we have to get it and
we've got it.
And that... that's awesome.
>> PROBST: Pete, did a leader
emerge yet, a clear leader, or
is it still a tribe?
>> Yeah, somebody did step up,
and I value the fact that Hunter
did step up because I wouldn't
have wanted it any other way.
He has been optimistic.
He has been open, asking each
and every one of us what we
suggest, and I really value and
respect that.
>> PROBST: Peter, feel like you
fit in with this group?
>> Actually, I never felt
comfortable.
Once I got on land, just didn't
feel quite right to me, and I
was very surprised.
I thought it was going to be a
piece of cake for me.
>> PROBST: Sarah, do you think
you have a role yet to find?
>> Kind of everything, we're all
just sticking together, doing
what needs to be done.
We're all come together like
that, but I mean, there are some
of us that are definitely better
at things than others, but I'm
just kind of jumping in.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Well, somebody always has the
distinction of being the first
person voted out of the tribe.
It's time to find out who that
person is.
Here's how it's going to work.
One by one, you guys are going
to make your way along the rock
path up to the voting
confessional.
You'll write down the name of
the person you're voting out in
clear letters, hold it up, state
the reason why you're voting for
that person.
Okay, it's time to vote.
Peter, you're first.
>> Tricia, you deserve to stay.
>> This person is a very nice
person, but he did a couple
things today that really kind of
threw me off.
So my vote is for Peter.
>> Sarah, I love you like a play
cousin.
I just don't think you was doing
your... your end of the bargain.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Peter.
Sarah.
Patricia.
Peter.
That's two votes Peter;
two votes Sarah;
one vote Patricia.
Peter.
Three votes Peter.
First person voted out of the
tribe: Peter.
No need to read the last vote.
We'll leave that a mystery.
Peter, you need to bring me your
torch.
Peter, the tribe has spoken.
>> Go get them.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
You survived your first vote.
Now go back and build your
world.
It's only been three days.
Anything can happen.
Head back to camp.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: At Maraamu...
>> Here's the plan:
Go gather some coconuts.
>> PROBST: ...Patricia takes
charge.
>> This is the tool tree.
We're going to leave the
machetes here.
>> She's doing too much talking.
>> PROBST: At Rotu, a hungry
tribe competes for the kill.
( whistles )
But it's Kathy that finds food.
>> Get out here.
I'm serious!
>> Sometimes I take myself a
little too seriously.
I wish I had heeded my wife's
advice of just come to this
island and have fun.
And truly, the other seven
contestants, I love them dearly
and I'll have fond memories of
this adventure.