>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Deep in the Pearl Islands,
16 Americans were surprised
by an all-new beginning
to the game.
You're going into this game with
nothing but the clothes you
have on your backs, just like
if you really were shipwrecked.
Split into two tribes,
Morgan and Drake,
they were given
100 Panamanian dollars
and a chance to barter
for supplies.
>> How much?
>> PROBST: The Morgan Tribe
scattered and argued with
the locals.
>> Give me my money back.
I don't want it.
>> PROBST: The Drakes fared
better with the help of
Sandra, who spoke Spanish...
>> Aquel me dijo dos Balboa.
>> PROBST: ...and Rupert,
who pirated Morgan's shoes.
>> Pirates pillage.
>> PROBST: With their new
supplies, the tribes set out
for their separate islands.
At their camp, the Morgans
continued to struggle,
this time with shelter
and water.
>> They say we'll go later
for the water.
Personally, we need to do it
now.
>> PROBST: At Drake,
Burton caught the first fish,
but Rupert showed him up
by bringing in a bounty.
>> I'm coming out here
to be the caretaker
and I think I'm doing it.
>> PROBST: At the first
immunity challenge...
Survivors ready?
Go!
...it was a close race
at the finish,
but the Drakes
pulled off a narrow victory.
Drake wins immunity!
The Morgan Tribe blamed
their loss on skinny Ryan.
>> That sucked.
Skinny Ryan, he just hasn't
been pulling his weight at camp
or at the challenge.
>> PROBST: And Tijuana got wind
of Nicole's last-minute
plotting.
>> You're not listening.
He told me, so I came
directly to you.
>> PROBST: At their first
tribal council, Nicole's
troublemaking caused her to be
the first person
voted out of the Pearl Islands.
Nicole, the tribe
has spoken.
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> When it comes time for night,
it's breaking us down.
Um, it's breaking me down,
I know.
It's very hard to not be able
to sleep.
It's very hard
to freeze every night.
And there's nothing you can do
about it.
The wind is coming...
you don't have any control.
It's beating all of us up.
It's freezing out here.
>> We need to... we need to get
a strong enough fire
that we'll be able
to get some heat.
I mean, I'm not expecting it
to be any Holiday Inn.
I mean, clearly not.
Just shivering every night,
that, that, uh...
that gets me.
And I know it's... to me,
it seems like it's only
a matter of time
before, you know,
something like pneumonia
or something like that
could settle in.
'Cause, I don't have
any clothes.
>> ( sighs ): Good night.
>> Good night.
>> Come on.
What's going on here?
( laughing )
A springboard for my head.
>> One of my biggest concerns
has been sleep deprivation.
We had one to two hours total
in three nights.
And, uh, you know, if we
don't solve that problem,
people are going
to start hallucinating.
>> Last night, I don't...
I don't even remember sleeping.
You know, I think I'm going
to be able to go.
Once I get a few bottles
of water in me
and a little bit of food,
I should be fine.
But I got to find a plan
for me, 'cause this isn't
working for me.
I'm going to try and come up
with a backup plan.
>> Skinny Ryan, his best day
doesn't equate to what I can do
on my worst day.
That's no knock on him.
It's just, physically,
he just has nothing to offer.
He just doesn't have
what it takes to...
to get it done.
>> Last night was 1,000 times
better than the night before.
>> As far as sleep goes?
>> As far as my whole
state of mind.
>> Yeah.
>> I am loving life
and loving this place
and loving the position I'm in.
I am in paradise.
What more do I want?
I'm living in a bounty of food.
I've got beautiful souls
around me.
>> You're doing a great job.
>> Oh, you are, too.
And I've got some help
being strong.
People are not
truly lazy per se.
People are having a hard time
in paradise.
( laughing )
>> Just jackass.
Did you not learn
how much is in
a coconut by now?
>> There's still a lot
in there, but maybe it's like,
uh, coconut oil.
Maybe it's like suntan lotion.
>> I love being in the middle
of a gigantic fish tank.
I love being able to go out
and, in a couple of hours,
bring a sack of fish home.
>> Okay, Burton...
>> Yo.
>> When it came back
today, it was... it was kind
of loose.
>> Yeah, I tightened it.
And when I was
spear-fishing yesterday, this
thing fell all the way off.
>> Oh, really?
>> Make sure that's always
tight, and when you're fishing,
check that and make sure
that's tight.
If we lose that...
>> I try to check in between.
>> ...we got no tools
to tighten it with.
>> Yeah.
It's more of a pain in the ass
for me to give him my spear
and worry about it being lost
or being, you know, broken
or whatever where I...
then I will be in trouble
because that's my food.
I need to eat meat.
>> That's pretty good, huh?
>> Man...
>> ( sighs ): I don't know if
I can eat anymore.
This is great.
>> Guys, that is yummy.
>> I'm full.
>> Tree mail, tree mail.
What, what?
The tree mail.
Ah, tree mail.
Oh, we just got some tree mail.
It's a big one for us.
And a super big one for me.
There may not be more pressure
for any survivor
in the history of Survivor to do
well at a challenge than me.
"Stormy weather,
ran ships aground
Most fortunes were lost,
A few, they were found
Salvage the quickest,
silver and gold,
You'll then be rewarded
like pirates of old."
( cheering )
>> There's all this talk
about how I didn't give 100%
in the last challenge.
And what really sucks is,
I gave more than 100%.
So now, I've got to come up
with some kind of extra,
extra strength that I may...
may not even have harnessed away
in this poor little body.
>> PROBST: Come on in, Drake.
Take a spot on your mat.
Morgan, come on in.
Drake, getting your first look
at the new Morgan Tribe,
minus Nicole, voted out
at the first Tribal Council.
Okay.
You ready for today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Big time.
>> PROBST: It is for a reward
and here's how it works.
Scattered along
the ocean floor,
marked by floating buoys,
are five treasure items.
One at a time,
a member from each tribe's
going to swim out,
dive down and retrieve an item.
There is also a treasure chest
on the ocean floor.
Once your tribe has all five
items in that chest,
and the fifth person
is back here at the start,
your entire tribe will then race
out, return the treasure chest.
First tribe to get
their treasure chest up
on the platform wins reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: It's two parts.
There's a shovel and a key.
These are yours to keep.
>> Yes!
>> All right!
>> This is nice.
>> PROBST: Buried on each
of your islands somewhere
is a treasure chest
with enough bounty to last you
for a long, long time.
The reward for today's
challenge: first clue,
piece of the map that will lead
you to your treasure chest.
This is the first
of three clues.
The winning tribe will also get
to loot, that is steal,
one item
from the other tribe's camp.
This will apply to all future
tribal reward challenges.
So you have something extra
to play for now.
Ready to get this going?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, Drake,
because you have one extra
member, you're sitting somebody
out-- who's sitting out?
Sandra, take a seat
on the bench.
Guys, take your spot,
wait for my "Go."
You guys ready?
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
( cheering )
>> Come on, Ryan!
>> Come on, Ryan.
( cheering )
>> Come on, Ryan!
>> PROBST: Drake with an early
big lead.
>> Go! Go!
( all shouting )
>> Why doesn't he tag out?
>> Come on, Ryan!
( cheering )
Come on, Ryan!
>> PROBST: Ryan!
You can bring the item
back and tag out!
( yelling )
You got to take the goblet,
put it in the chest,
then get your item.
Ryno decides
to not take the mask.
Drake with two items,
Morgan still trying to get
their first one in the chest.
>> Go, Rupert!
>> PROBST: Drake with three
items.
Christa heading for the fourth.
Morgan with one.
>> Come on, Ryno!
>> PROBST: Christa with another
item for Drake.
>> Okay, I got it.
>> Yes, Chris, yes!
>> All right! Let's go!
>> Come on, Morgan!
>> PROBST: Drake needs one more
item.
Burton, you're going to get
the bowl to put it in.
The bowl is your last item.
Ryno's worn out, passing off
the pearls to Lill.
>> PROBST: All seven, go get the
chest.
Lock it up and bring it back.
Morgan's still working on
their third item.
>> That's it, Lill, come on.
>> All right, let's go get it.
Ready?
Three.
>> PROBST: Andrew is heading out
to get another item for Morgan.
>> One, two, go!
( grunting )
>> Wait, wait, wait.
( yelling )
>> PROBST: Open it up.
Let's see your items.
You need all five.
Drake wins reward!
( cheering )
>> Whoo, baby!
>> One, two, three,
Drake!
>> PROBST: Drake, great
teamwork-- you guys worked
together, you had a great plan,
you didn't give up.
Here's the first clue
to your buried treasure chest.
You'll both head back to camp,
then Drake, you will decide
which member's going
to give Morgan a visit.
And you can help yourself
to one item from their camp.
( cheering )
>> ( chanting ): Drake! Drake!
Drake! Drake!
( chanting continues )
>> I'm guessing this
is a third of the map.
>> What's the back say?
>> "There's a treasure buried,
so be on your way.
Make sure you leave
at the right time of day.
You'll be heading east,
travel by land,
and don't plan to stop
when you run out of sand."
>> So, when they say,
"run out of sand,"
they're talking about right
there where it turns to rock.
>> It's really exciting
knowing that there's
treasure out there.
We're just...
our hands are tied right now
'cause it's high tide
and we can't do anything.
But as soon as it's low tide,
we're going to go out there
because who knows
what could be in there.
And I'm sure, whatever it is,
it could be beneficial.
>> We need to figure out who's
going to the camp to take
their stuff.
>> Well, I don't know if
anyone else is in agreeance,
but if I could think of
one thing we don't have...
We need a water jug
like the one that we ruined,
because if we could
fill that thing up...
>> Also something to keep
in mind, though, if...
if they have more
than one water jug
and if all they have is a tarp,
it would be good to hurt them
by taking their tarp.
>> Honestly, we don't
need to hurt them.
>> You can live by being wet.
>> We don't need to hurt them.
>> I'd let Sandra go.
Okay, cool.
>> Sandra, I'm for it.
>> Good.
>> No matter who goes,
if you're a nice person or not,
if you had another tribe member
come up to your camp
and take something of yours,
you wouldn't like them either.
I was happy that she went
rather than myself.
>> Pirate good, baby.
Pirate good.
>> Oh, my God!
I can't breathe.
( laughs )
>> They kicked our butts today.
And one of the reasons
it hurts so much
is because we did so miserably.
We are at a subsistence level
right now.
I mean, we're just getting by.
So, when some little punk from
Drake comes by here to take
one of our items, it doesn't
sound like a big deal.
But when you're living this,
it's huge.
>> What if the little
motormouth from Drake
says he wants our tarp?
>> Hell, no.
Are you-- oh.
There is no ifs, ands or buts
about it-- he takes that tarp,
I'm going home.
I'm not lying.
( laughing )
>> So, how y'all doing?
Are you the ambassador
of the Morgan Tribe?
>> I'm the goober
of the Morgan Tribe.
>> Why do you say that?
I'm Sandra.
>> I'm Ryan.
Good job today.
>> You guys doing okay?
>> We're doing good.
How are you?
>> I'm Sandra.
>> Congratulations today.
>> Sander?
>> Sandra.
>> Sandra, Andrew.
>> Ryan.
>> Nice to meet you.
This is nice.
>> How does it compare
to your camp?
>> Ours is nice, too.
When I arrived at...
at the Morgan Tribe,
I could not believe
that they...
they just didn't have anything.
It's unbelievable.
I don't know how
they're getting through.
We managed to buy
a lot of stuff
at the village.
I mean, we bought tons
of stuff at the village.
So...
So, there's more stuff.
Where's the rest of it?
And so I looked around
and I went looking
for the water jug.
Where the ...
is the water jug?
Well, they had no water jug.
So I said, "Wait a minute."
>> Did you make a decision yet?
>> Yeah.
I want that baby up there.
The tarp.
>> Okay, you're going to have
to take it down yourself, right?
>> Yep.
>> I have to take it
down myself?
>> Absolutely.
>> Okay.
>> Go ahead.
>> Damn, I didn't think
I'd come out here to work.
>> She's going to ruin it.
I'm going to lay it
nice and neat
so you guys can fix it back up.
I'll be done in a minute and
I'll be out of you guys's hair.
In order for me
to get the tarp,
I had to destroy
their whole shelter,
which I started feeling bad
until they started
running their mouths.
Can I use one of the knives?
>> No.
>> These are our knives.
>> I go to a grab a knife
and the black girl's like,
"No, no, no, no, no.
"You're not going
to use our knife
and you better not
cut our rope."
So I was like, "Okay.
Regardless...
I'm taking the tarp down."
>> Do what yoygot to do.
>> Not a problem.
>> Don't wreck the shelter,
okay?
>> No, no, no.
Hey, I got to do
what I got to do,
right?
>> No, not necessarily.
>> Wrapped around...
look, there we go.
It's not that bad.
It's all good.
But look, it's coming
apart fairly easy.
>> Sandra came over
and she was just...
I don't know.
That whole tribe is just...
is a bunch of ( bleep ).
I didn't do
any unnecessary harm.
You guys will have this up
in no time, I'm sure.
>> She acted like she was nice
about taking the tarp.
But I think she was a little bit
too snatchy about it
and tore it down
kind of on purpose.
>> You don't know how good you
have it until you see others.
Well, you guys sleep tight.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
And, uh, no hard feelings
and I'll see you guys tomorrow,
okay? Take care.
>> Bye-bye.
She's such a bitch.
>> Andrew... it's getting dark.
>> I know.
>> Let's...
( thunder rumbling )
>> We all need to get
in the shelter.
>> But I'm going to help
with the shelter.
We're gonna get this
all done first.
>> We'll have time
to talk after that.
>> All right, we're going
to get this all done first.
>> Everyone was devastated
by the loss of our tarp
and Osten was
throwing in the towel.
He was finished.
He was ready to walk off.
We need people around
that are on the ups,
that are digging this game.
And this is great stuff.
We don't need people
just walking around,
"I don't... I want to go home,"
you know.
It's a real morale-killer
for the tribe.
>> Well, let's look at
the reality here.
There's so many things
and aspects to the game.
When it comes down
to it, it's mental.
>> I'm in here in shorts, and
it's gonna be raining and cold.
I'm gonna get sick,
and I could
potentially get pneumonia;
I've gotten it before.
I'm just not gonna...
I just don't feel
that-that I need that.
>> Yeah, but you're saying
you-you may be.
You don't know.
>> I will be at the end of
this, tonight.
>> Osten had mentioned to me
that he was potentially thinking
about quitting.
And I just wanted to talk
to him in a calm fashion
and truly understand
and then give him
my personal opinion.
My opinion is that
you're giving up.
You would be a loss,
not only for us,
but for me.
We're here in this together.
I'm just asking you
just to try, at least.
>> All right.
>> And that means
being here tonight
throughout the
whole night.
>> All right.
I'm gonna let that
marinate a little bit.
>> I think I'm done now.
I've made my peace;
I've said what I needed to say.
It's up to him,
what he wants to do.
Only he knows
what's best for him.
>> It's impossible.
You can't even swim out there.
>> Really?
You see anything cool?
>> Went fishing,
to catch some fish, and I was
out there in the, um,
heavy tides and the currents.
Shot the spear, and, um,
the tip winded up coming off
and, um,
either got lodged under a rock
or is swirling around somewhere
in the tide.
But I just couldn't swim
anymore,
so I had to come back in
and break the news.
Yeah, we have a problem.
>> What's wrong?
>> This. My spear is dead.
Where is the spear?
You didn't even get it?
It'll go to the bottom.
>> I looked all over.
The tide's so hard,
it keeps whipping me
back out to sea.
>> The current was so strong,
and it was throwing him
into the rocks, and...
Now, remember this is
in our little inlet
where it's a bathtub.
He couldn't find the spearhead.
He gives up.
That's why I wanted...
that's why I was...
>> I kept tightening it, too.
I wanted to be the
only one that did that.
You lost my bag and
you killed my spear.
>> And I didn't do it
on purpose.
>> I know. I know.
Can I be mad?
>> Yes, you can be mad.
But do you want to come
help me find it?
>> That is gonna ... us.
>> I know.
>> That right there
is gonna ... us.
>> I know.
Trust me, I know.
That's why I've been looking
for the last hour.
I had a little mishap, and
I lost the tip of the spear.
When I confronted Rupert,
he kind of freaked out a little
because he, you know,
he got attached to that as well.
That became his little thing,
you know, catching fish.
And I was pretty upset about it
because, you know,
I do care about
what others think, of course,
and I know how
certain people feel.
>> That is our meat.
That is our best meat source.
>> Well, can we just
make a pact, then,
not for Shawn to go
fishing with the spear?
>> Oh...!
>> No, I mean, I don't know
how to go spearfishing.
If you would try, you know,
like everyone else,
then, you know, it's a chance
you're gonna lose something.
I mean, you know?
It's try or not try.
>> Shawn is the biggest puss I
have ever met in my entire life.
>> But I say, as a tribe, we go
out there and try and find it.
>> Absolutely.
>> I mean, I don't mind
going back out by myself.
>> That is more...
That is as important to me
as that damn treasure chest.
My spear is gone,
the head is gone.
There's no more meat.
They're talking about
tying the damn fork off to it.
He could not even tell me
where he lost it at.
So I go out and I start
doing a grid pattern.
I start from the trees, start
from where I know he wasn't,
and on my grid pattern,
I'd do about a size
of a football field.
You're looking
at a general area
that's five or six
football fields.
>> Yes!
>> Where was it?
>> In the ocean!
>> Where in the ocean?
( laughing )
>> I am so happy.
Yes...!
Drake...!
I feel better.
I stopped yelling and screaming
at him and cussing at him
and calling him bad names.
Do they know we found it?
>> I think they heard you yell
and they assumed.
( laughing )
They assume you did,
but I had to come and confirm.
>> I know finding that spear
made him feel better.
If we hadn't have
found the spear,
he, for sure, would have been
done, done, done.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Welcome.
You guys doing all right?
>> Yep.
>> Great!
>> Doing good.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Let me ask about the looting--
who ended up going over
from Drake?
>> I went over.
>> PROBST: How'd it feel to be a
pirate?
>> It felt good to be a pirate.
>> PROBST: Just remember,
payback can be painful.
Okay, give me back
the Immunity Idol.
Immunity, back up for grabs.
Win immunity, your tribe is safe
from Tribal Council
for another three days.
For today's challenge,
three tribe members
from each tribe
will become prisoners
for the other tribe.
One person will have
their hands tied.
They will be on a raft
leaning against a pole.
The other two will be
draped across the raft--
their hands will be tied.
Using a rope-and-pulley system,
the other four members
from the opposing tribe
will pull as fast as they can,
taking you out to sea.
Meanwhile, the guy on the raft
is untying his hands
as quickly as he can.
Once he's untied himself,
he can then untie
the other two tribe members
who are draped across the raft.
When you're all three untied,
you swim
back to shore,
bringing with you
two ropes and the bamboo chute
which is tied to your raft.
Inside that bamboo chute
are compass points.
Go inside the compass ring.
You'll use the compass points
and your two ropes.
Where the ropes intersect
is a tribe flag.
Dig down, get it up
and get it in its sleeve.
The first tribe
to raise their tribe flag
and have all members with a hand
on the flag wins immunity.
Drake, you're sitting somebody
out-- esterday it was Sandra;
today it's Christa.
Everybody else strategize,
wait for my "go."
All right, the prisoners
for the Drake Tribe,
Rupert, Michelle and Trish,
will be pulled out to sea
by the Morgan Tribe.
Andrew, Ryno and Darrah,
you'll be pulled out
by the Drake Tribe--
immunity at stake.
Survivors ready?
>> Ready.
>> PROBST: Go!
>> Let's go, let's go.
>> PROBST: It's a race to see
who can get untied first
and back to shore.
>> PROBST: That a way to pull,
Morgan!
Andrew and Rupert
are both untied.
They're trying to untie
their teammates.
It's gonna be a race
back to shore.
Keep pulling.
>> Keep going, guys.
>> Here's mine.
>> PROBST: Andrew's got
everybody done-- he's going for
the bamboo chute.
>> Pull! Pull!
>> PROBST: Andrew trying to
untie the clue.
Rupert has his clue.
Both tribe members are free.
Morgan swimming in.
Bring your ropes.
>> Go!
>> Let's go!
You guys are doing it!
Let's go!
>> PROBST: Morgan comes ashore
with a huge lead.
All right, give me
the coordinates.
>> PROBST: Go!
Start solving it.
Get in the ring.
>> Let's go!
Come on, run, run!
You guys got it!
Good job!
>> Nobody panic.
>> PROBST: Everybody's got
to get here first.
>> Come on!
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: That a way, be
patient.
Morgan struggling to
get their coordinates open.
>> Get to your coordinates.
>> You got it.
Morgan still trying to get
their clue open.
Drake has their
first coordinate.
>> Down here.
Northwest to east.
>> Northwest south.
>> PROBST: Morgan finally has
their clue open.
Find the intersect!
Dig!
Start digging!
>> Get out of the way.
Get out of the way.
>> PROBST: Don't quit.
Dig deep.
>> Let's go, guys.
Let's go!
>> PROBST: Drake has their flag
out.
>> Pick it up!
Come on, you guys!
>> Here we go!
>> Plug it in!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Drake wins immunity!
>> Yeah!
( cheering, shouting )
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: Great effort.
Drake, once again,
immunity going back to camp.
( cheering )
>> Okay, guys, touch it.
Touch it.
>> PROBST: Next time I see you
guys will be at Tribal Council.
You can head back to camp.
See you in a while.
>> We lost immunity challenge
today.
Tribal Council tonight.
Tribe's pretty devastated,
actually.
Of course,
the critical decision tonight
is who's going to go?
Who's leaving the Morgan Tribe?
( thunder rumbling )
>> At first,
when Osten told me that
he wanted to quit,
I was really shocked.
But then,
the more I thought about it,
the more it made sense.
This is a game where you've got
to have your whole heart
into this and it just doesn't
seem like he's got it.
It's only day six.
>> What's happening?
>> It's between
Skinny Ryan and me.
>> Huh?
If you're gone, we got no hope.
If you think
about Osten's strength,
his physical strength is huge.
We can't compete with,
you know, Grizzly Adams,
and those other two horses.
Without Osten?
It's impossible.
I mean, it's
clear over here.
The clouds are
going this way.
>> Enough's enough.
Feel like...
sleep out in the cold
just until I get pneumonia?
Just to win a million dollars?
And, if I don't win it,
then I got fluid in my lungs,
potentially, blood in my lungs.
It doesn't matter who you are.
You have no control
over your body.
If your body wants to make
you stop, you're stopping.
>> You know what?
Osten didn't win,
so he wants to quit.
How fair is that?
Osten's excuse was
his body was giving out.
I saw him on the beach.
He's running up and down,
throwing coconuts,
lifting logs, playing.
There's nothing wrong
with his body.
That's a piss-poor
attitude, isn't it?
>> Uh-huh.
>> He just got beat,
and he couldn't take being beat.
>> Did Osten come to you
and talk to you?
>> He came up to me and asked
me, face-to-face,
"Would you please vote
for me tonight?"
>> He told you that tonight?
>> Yeah.
Like, I'd say, less
than 30 minutes ago.
>> I was personally upset
and disappointed with Osten
for quitting.
I just can't understand.
I just can't fathom it.
>> You mean, vote myself off?
I thought about it, yeah,
but I don't know yet.
>> He has what it takes,
in my opinion.
That's what pisses me off.
It's because I care about him.
How can you cut yourself short?
You know, you got here.
When it comes down to it,
if that's the decision
that he makes, then it is
his heart that's not here.
And if that's the case,
he would have to go.
>> PROBST: Here we go again.
I know you guys don't
want to be back here.
So, Andrew, what are
the camp issues right now?
>> Still sleeping, Jeff.
The floor of our
shelter is still
not as comfortable
as it needs to be.
We had to rebuild
the whole roof because
Sandra from the Drake Tribe
came and, uh...
took our tarp,
which was our whole roof.
>> PROBST: But Sandra took
the tarp yesterday.
So what did you do for the
first five days? Ryan?
I mean, what's going on?
This is the second time
at Tribal Council
we've talked about sleep issues.
>> Uh, I... I think we're
kind of hurting in focus.
I don't think we've
ever actually sat down,
come up with an agenda, and
actually followed it through.
I think there needs to be more
teamwork, more unification.
>> PROBST: So Andrew, when...
when you look at this tribe,
they sort of appointed
you the leader.
You know, they sacrifice leaders
in some cultures that are as
decimated as this tribe is.
When is this going to change?
Because it isn't going
to get any easier out here.
>> Yeah, I know.
It's going to change tomorrow.
We're going to--
first thing in the morning--
finish the floor
to where we get a solid sleep.
No more sleep deprivation,
hallucinations,
mentally shutting down--
all that stuff.
And we're just going
to take care of it tomorrow.
Enough is enough.
>> PROBST: Lill, as
a lifelong scoutmaster,
assess this tribe.
If this was your
pack of Boy Scouts,
how do they rank?
I would give them an A+
for spirit.
You have to understand,
the last two challenges, we were
this close to winning.
I don't think,
if the spirit's not there...
>> PROBST: Whoa. Wait a second.
The reward challenge, you guys
would still be out there.
So you weren't close to winning.
Assess the tribe.
You guys, you aren't sleeping,
you've lost every
challenge so far.
Give me some truth here
about the tribe.
There's a problem somewhere.
Where is it,
from your point of view?
>> The only thing that I think
that we ought to be doing
is maybe fishing a little more.
>> PROBST: That's all you see?
Anybody here want
to own up to the fact
that they're a little...
they're a little on edge about
being out here?
>> Listen, I ain't going
to lie to you.
Normally, under
normal circumstances,
I would not be here.
Absolutely not.
>> PROBST: So, once Survivor is
over, however long
you last, you won't anytime soon
be going on another trek?
>> Absolutely not.
No. No doubt about it.
>> PROBST: Again, you have
to vote somebody
out tonight.
It's a big vote.
You can't continue
to lose tribe members.
So, Lill, what do you base
the vote on tonight?
I would base my vote on who has,
uh... contributed
to the troop--
I'm sorry-- to the tribe,
whether or not
they have accepted
defeat, or did they just
give up and say,
"This isn't for me."
That would be what my...
my vote would be for.
>> PROBST: Andrew, how
about for you?
It's tough.
What's your vote going
to be based on?
>> I look for the weakest link.
And I... I don't
care if you're 100 pounds.
I don't care
if you're 250 pounds.
Who's bringing the tribe down?
Who's not laying it all
on the line
and willing to just go crazy
to get it done
to further the tribe.
That's my analysis, and that's
how I'm voting tonight.
>> PROBST: Ryan, how
about for you?
>> Uh... normally, I would go
for, uh... whatever
the weakest person, uh...
physically.
But, uh... a person
came up to me today and, uh...
told me that they...
they were ready to go,
so that's probably
what I'm going to base mine on.
>> PROBST: So somebody came to
you today and said they're ready
to go, meaning they want
out of the game?
>> Right.
You going to tell me
who that is?
>> Of course not.
>> PROBST: We'll see how it
plays out.
It is time to vote.
Andrew, you're first.
>> Osten, I think you're great,
but you gave up on us.
You're the one
who's saying, "My big burly body
has shut down."
I don't believe
it was because of your body.
So I'm voting for you tonight.
>> Ryan, you're a great kid.
You got a bunch of heart.
You just don't have
the strength for this game,
and I'll see you
when I'm out of here.
>> You would have never
gotten this vote if you hadn't
asked me to.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave
the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Osten.
Skinny Ryan.
Two votes Osten.
One vote Ryan.
Ryan.
That's two votes Ryan,
two votes Osten.
Three votes Ryan,
The second member voted out
of the Morgan Tribe,
Skinny Ryan.
That's four votes.
That's enough.
Last vote will remain a mystery.
You need to bring me your torch.
Ryan, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> PROBST: You can head back to
camp-- good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> Osten? He quit.
>> There's a big difference
between quitting
and pulling the trigger.
>> PROBST: At Drake, the hunt is
on.
>> I want to find that treasure
so bad.
>> PROBST: And there's trouble
in paradise.
>> You know what?
I can get loud, too!
What the...?!
>> I don't want to...
argue with you!
>> Screw Jon. He's an ass.
>> I think I lost
this game in the, uh...
first five minutes
I was out here,
'cause I didn't make friends
with the right people.
It was really hard
turning things around.
I wish I would
have just gone and just tried to
be friends with everybody.
I'm upset that the
ride's already over.
This is a game I
know inside and out.
I would have to say that I'm
kind of disappointed in myself
and I'm not sure I gave it 100%.
Sorry if I let anybody down.