>> JEFF PROBST: We're on board
the Rembrandt van Rijn,
heading south off the coast of
Panama to a remote
location
in the Pacific waters
of Central America.
Down below, 16 Americans
who have no idea the
adventure
of a lifetime has already begun.
After traveling all night,
they arrived Panama City
early this morning,
boarded this vessel,
suitcases still in tow,
still wearing the same clothes
they had on on the plane.
Right now, they're relaxing
under the false assumption
that we are several days away
from starting the game.
They think we're heading out
to take publicity photos.
What they don't know,
this game has already
started,
and it is full of surprises.
For instance, those
suitcases,
so carefully packed with
essential outdoor
clothing--
worthless.
The only clothes
they're going to be taking
are the clothes on their
back.
And more twists await.
Their destination--
the Pearl Islands--
a land with a bloody
history
of looting and piracy.
Brutal battles took place
in
these waters as pirates preyed
on unsuspecting ships,
plundering their gold, silver
and pearls.
( pirates shouting )
The jungles, which were
the
perfect hideout for these
pirates, are rugged.
The weather, temperamental.
The waters here are home
to some of the most magnificent,
but deadly, marine life
anywhere in the Pacific Ocean.
Sharks, stingrays, eels,
even whales thrive in a
spectacular world beneath
the
sea.
This will be their home
for the next 39 days.
They must learn to adapt,
or they'll be voted out
of the tribe.
In the end, only one will
remain to claim the
million-
dollar prize.
39 days, 16 people...
one survivor.
( theme song playing )
♪ ♪
Welcome, guys, to Survivor:
Pearl Islands.
The game is on.
We're starting right now.
I know everybody here brought
their suitcases,
I know you got a lot more
luggage downstairs.
And it's true, in the past,
survivors have been
allowed
to go through their luggage
and pick out a few
essential
items.
You guys won't have that
luxury.
( nervous giggling )
You're going into this
game
with the clothes you have
on your back...
just like if you really
were shipwrecked.
>> He says, "The game starts,
you're taking nothing."
I was like, "Oh..."
>> Looking at the
wardrobe,
I got to say, a couple of nice
suits up here.
( laughing )
>> I'm wearing an Armani
suit.
How am I going to get by?
What am I going to do
with a suit?
>> PROBST: A very cute
strapless
dress-- I hope you're wearing
something under that.
( laughter )
>> I was like, "Okay,
well,
this is fine.
"You know, I don't have a
bra
on; I hope my dress stays up."
>> PROBST: I'm sure the
Boy
Scouts of America will be glad
to see they're
represented.
( laughing )
When it comes to your
footwear,
however, I took the liberty
of going through your
suitcases.
Here are your tennis shoes.
I want you to have a
fighting
chance at the challenges.
Okay.
Now, I need to get
your personal items.
I want everything.
Start getting it out--
watches,
wallets, money, passports
and any jewelry you don't
want
to lose...
I want in here.
Bags are staying behind,
so you don't need to
go through your bags,
just anything else.
( laughter )
You were really hoping,
weren't you?
>> I was hoping.
Hey, there's a snowball's chance
in hell that I thought you
guys
would let me bring this.
>> PROBST: Put it in
there.
Okay, your tribe names--
going to be based on
two of the most notorious
pirates in Panamanian
history--
the Drake Tribe, after Sir
Francis Drake, and the
Morgan
Tribe, after Henry Morgan.
So, as I call out your
name,
you'll come forward,
we'll divide into tribes.
First up: Shawn... wearing blue.
First member of the Drake
Tribe.
Have a spot right over here.
Darrah...
wearing orange.
First member of the Morgan
Tribe.
Have a spot over here.
Christa, next member
of the Drake Tribe.
Come on up, Christa.
Osten, come on up.
Look at that loot.
( laughter )
That is pirate-like.
You got booze, music.
>> That's booty.
>> PROBST: Rupert, next
member
of the Drake Tribe.
Have a spot.
Welcome.
>> Rupert is the man.
I thought, "This dude is cool.
"He's a big old hippie,
and, uh, he looks strong as an
ox."
>> PROBST: Next member
of the Morgan Tribe...
Boy Scout, Lill.
Welcome.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Next member of
the Drake Tribe: Trish.
Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Next member of
the Morgan Tribe: Ryan.
Welcome.
Next member of the Drake Tribe:
Burton.
Next member for the Morgan
Tribe: Tijuana.
Look at those heels.
>> Tijuana, she's
unbelievable.
She's a Nubian princess.
That's how good-looking she
is.
>> PROBST: Next member of the
Drake Tribe: Michelle.
Welcome.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Next member of
Morgan: Ryan.
We have two Ryans.
Wearing blue for the Drake
Tribe: Jon.
( applause )
>> Jon!
>> I go by the moniker of
Jonny Fairplay.
I don't play fair.
What's up, big boys?!
Let me hear it!
>> PROBST: The Morgan Tribe's
about to be very happy.
Here's the woman
who's wearing nothing
under her dress--
come on down, Nicole.
>> Found a new use for this
thing.
>> PROBST: You're right.
Works as a great tube top.
Personal items, please.
And you're over there.
Give me those personal items.
Last member of the Drake
Tribe:
Sandra.
( clapping )
Last member of the Morgan Tribe:
Andrew.
Sporting a nice tie and an
expensive suit.
>> Thanks, man.
>> PROBST: Now, if you
thought
the clothing issue was tough,
it's about to get worse,
because when you arrive
at your camp, there's
nothing
waiting for you there, either.
Nothing-- no food
whatsoever,
not the first bit of tools,
no flint and steel
to start fire.
I mean zip.
What I can offer you, though,
is this--
the opportunity to control
your own fate.
100 Balboas in here--
that's Panamanian money.
Behind me... small fishing
village.
You're in luck, it's market day.
I'm not going to lie to
you.
It's a small village,
there's not a lot there,
but if you're smart
and you have a plan,
you can get everything
you need-- the essentials
to
help you survive 39 days.
Explore this village.
There's a lot of nooks and
crannies, knock on doors.
When you run out of money,
barter with what you have,
which is, granted,
not much, but use it.
You're not coming back here.
Map to your new home.
You must set aside enough money
to hire a boat and a
driver
to get you to your camps.
You each will have your
own
island, and they are a long
ways away.
You need to be there by sundown.
Got a lot to accomplish
in the next few hours.
You're going to have
to work together
as a tribe to pull it off.
I wish you the very best of
luck.
>> I was like, "Oh, my God.
What have I done?"
This is beyond what
I bargained for.
I knew it was going to be
the adventure of a
lifetime.
I didn't know it was going to be
this big of an adventure
of a lifetime.
>> PROBST: Drake, there's
a life ring.
Morgan, there's a life
ring.
If you needed a reason
to get in, here it is!
There go the shoes.
Go, guys!
( all clamoring )
>> PROBST: Life ring.
Somebody better get
your life ring, or you're
never gonna make it in.
Better not dilly-dally.
♪ ♪
>> I don't get in the
water.
I respect the water.
( laughs )
Unless I absolutely have to,
and I had to.
And I'm not, like, that
strong of a swimmer,
so I was in a state of shock.
I was like, "Oh, my Lord.
I could be in some...
a world of hurt right
now."
>> Are you okay?
>> I never would have
thought
swimming with my clothes on
would have been so hard,
but
it was.
With my big denim jeans,
my legs were rubber.
It took all I had to keep
kicking and getting it to shore.
I was spent, and it hadn't
even
started yet.
( chuckles )
>> The girls, they're... they're
running off, so...
>> Okay.
>> ...so we have to carry
the...
>> I'll carry their crap.
>> All right.
>> We didn't come to shore
together at all.
I was hoping that we would
come together with some
plans
and some goals, uh,
what we wanted to go to
first,
but that wasn't the case at all.
Uh, some of the girls took
off.
>> Do you know where we can
get a boat?
>> And, uh, Ryno, he-he just
took off.
He was gone-- it's like he
wasn't even part of the
tribe.
He was gone and he had his own
mission.
I don't even remember him
consulting anybody about
it.
>> Fire?
Flint?
>> No, no, no.
>> No?
>> Uh, boat?
>> Boat? Yes, yes.
>> Okay.
I wanted to check out
the village and get to certain
places and find where stuff
was
first and also try to find
where the boat was.
And I run all the way down
to the boat dock,
and I didn't have a map.
I didn't have any money
to pay this guy.
What's the most to go
pretty
much anywhere?
I forgot my map.
>> Nadie habla ingles.
>> Screwed up this one.
( indistinct voices )
>> All right, someone sit on
it
for a minute.
>> Well, here, here's our
group.
>> All right.
Stay here with this,
Rupert.
You watch it.
Let's get the money.
Where's the money?
We need it.
>> When I got to those stairs,
I was done.
We sit the sucker down,
and I needed to rest.
The other team, Morgan,
came up, sat their stuff
down
next to us, and all left.
This is definitely
a pirate adventure.
Pirates pillage, pirates
steal,
pirates take advantage.
If they were gonna be
silly enough to put it
right next to me,
I'm gonna put it in my thing.
All their trade goods,
all the little
women's shoes, the
insoles.
Everything that I could find
in theirs, I took.
I've always said I will lie,
cheat and steal
to win this game.
We're going on.
There was my stealing.
I stole for the Drake.
Take them, take them.
You know, get anything.
>> Whose are these?
>> Pirated.
>> Oh.
>> Feel that. Feel that.
Feel that.
For a knife? For a knife?
For a pineapple?
Shoes...
>> ¿Cambiarlo por eso?
>> Pineapple? Yeah?
We are pirates... so we pirated.
Yeah, it's a hard life,
living the pirate's life.
>> We got water.
>> We got water?
Okay, we need, um...
>> Machete?
>> We got, we got,
we got knives, we got knives.
>> We need flint steel?
>> How 'bout food?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Fishing stuff.
Where's the fishing stuff?
Hold on, let me ask this lady.
The way we attacked
getting
our supplies at the village
was, uh, a bit chaotic.
It was confusion.
>> Rice? Rice?
>> Rice.
>> Hey, Ryan, how many
candles?
>> You want to buy a belt?
By chance?
Buy a belt.
Stand up real quick, come
on.
Stand up, come here.
We only had a limited
amount
of money, so I made an
impulsive decision to sell
my clothes to benefit my tribe.
Slide them right in there.
Look at that.
That's unbelievable.
That looks... that looks great.
How, how...
I sell it to you?
Dos Balboas.
Thank you, partner.
I appreciate it.
You know, you got
to fast-talk some people.
And I was willing to try
to do whatever it took
to-to make the sale
so that we could have
more money for my group
to do whatever we needed
to do with the money.
>> Let me, uh, let me
talk...
Can I talk to two girls real
quick?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Just a little strategy.
Come here.
>> I'm listening, too.
>> Okay, come on.
( speaking indistinctly )
But you know old, old men
are real horny.
So, maybe sometimes if we don't
have money, flash your
boobs--
give 'em a quick peek or
something like that, all
right?
I don't mean to be rude,
but that-that could help.
>> Osten goes, "You know, girls,
"we don't necessarily
have to spend our money.
"With these old guys.
"they're really horny,
so you can just show them
your boobs."
He didn't even know our
names,
really yet, or-or us at all.
That was his first, you
know,
introduction to us.
So I was just, like,
"This guy's a jerk."
( cheering )
( speaking Spanish )
>> Hey, guys.
Wanna buy...?
>> Dos Balboas.
( speaking Spanish )
>> Okay, let's go.
We'll come back.
>> Yeah.
>> He wants three and three,
but the guy told us
two up there.
We buy the rice from him.
>> Sandra, she was so amazing
in the town, because she
spoke
the language and worked out all
these incredible deals.
And we would...
it wouldn't have been
possible.
( speaking Spanish )
>> Hola!
>> When we got to the village,
I
was lucky that I knew Spanish.
And I was trying to
bargain
with the lady at the store
and ask people for certain
things.
>> What's the cheapest
lantern?
And do they...?
( Sandra speaking Spanish
)
>> Por favor.
She'll do it for your
eyes.
>> Oh, gracias!
>> Your eyes for her...
>> Gracias! Oh!
>> The lady at the store
had it in for Trisha.
Trisha thought the lady
was laughing and giggling
with her or whatever.
But the lady actually, I think,
you know, liked her in a
sexual way.
There's, uh, Trisha
hugging
the lady, laughing and giggling
like it's all good.
And I'm like, "Yo, we need to
go."
You got to stay with her.
We're gonna leave you
here for a few minutes.
>> I feel that the village
people really respected Sandra
because she was being nice
and decent about things
and respectful,
unlike the other tribe
that was screaming at
people.
>> Give me my money back.
Money.
I need my money back.
I don't want it.
Money.
Okay, if y'all gonna
steal from me,
I'm gonna steal from
y'all.
>> Yeah, this is the one
we paid for.
>> Gracias, gracias.
>> We, we... we gave the
money.
We... No, no...
>> Gracias.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no.
>> Then don't do this!
Don't do this!
>> No, no, no, no, no.
>> Where's the money at?
>> Where's our money?
>> No, no.
>> Sí!
>> Muy poquito.
>> We're walking out with
the merchandise we paid for,
then another person says,
"No, you didn't pay for it"?!
Wait, what?
I-I'm sorry?
So, it definitely was a
difficult situation,
especially when you don't
know
all of the words
that you need to say.
No!
>> No, no, no.
>> Where's the money?
>> Hey, hey, she, she just
told
you she gave you the money.
>> No, no, no.
>> Sí! You're stealing.
>> I don't really get
along
with Tijuana.
She seemed, like,
extremely
overexcited about certain
things, and that was just
frustrating for me.
>> Where's the money?
Okay, where's the money?
( overlapping shouts )
>> We handled it to the best
of our ability.
And in the end, they came out
on top by saying,
"Basically,
we'll give this to you."
>> Okay, God will bless
you.
>> So it worked out well.
( singing and clapping )
>> We went around the corner,
and there was this lady
having... they were dancing.
She was having a barbecue,
and I says, "You know,
I'll give you this gold
chain
for everything you have here."
And she looked at my
chain,
she was like, "Yeah."
I put the chain around her
neck, and she was like,
"What do you want?"
I said, "I want all your
chicken, I want your
aluminum
foil.
I want your ketchup, your
hot sauce, the barbecue sauce."
She had a cutting board,
a knife.
Everything.
The only thing we didn't take
was the grill.
>> Yo, Blackbeard!
>> Oh, you won't
believe...
>> She just traded her necklace.
>> For my gold chain.
>> For her gold chain,
we have...
>> I got knives...
>> Oh, my God!
>> Ketchup, hot sauce...
>> I was definitely pissed
to see the Drake Tribe and all
of the wealth that they'd
come
into, all of the fortune.
That definitely just kind
of deflates you a little bit,
like, "Man, we could have
done that."
We could have been
even more prepared.
They were taking their
time,
and we weren't.
Okay, we got
to get down there.
Let's get all our group--
it's a long walk.
Come on.
You need help carrying
or you good?
>> I got it.
>> Let's rock.
>> Where we going?
We got tons of money.
>> All right. Hey, Osten!
We got tons of money!
>> We got money.
>> We had money left over.
Are we going to the boat now?
Can we go get more-more
fruit?
We have more money.
We should have spent
absolutely
all of the money.
I don't think we, uh,
fundamentally did-did
the right, right decision.
I think, I think we could have
gotten a few more good
supplies.
I think people
were just too anxious
to get on the boat and get-get
the thing started.
>> You said 35, so...
>> Treinta y cinco.
>> Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Okay, we're loading right now.
As far as getting enough of
what
we need, only time will tell.
( snorting )
>> Let's see, we have rice,
we have beans, we have a
container for the rice.
>> We got coconuts.
We got another chicken.
>> You know, I don't know
what more we need, really.
>> We did very well
in the village.
You know, we, we managed
to get a ton of stuff
for the little bit
of money we had.
>> We got fishing line,
a bunch of hooks.
I know we got a fishing
spear,
uh, for catching fish.
Um, we got wine,
we got a-a huge tarp,
we got two machetes,
which are essential.
>> We did good. We did
good.
>> We got so much.
I can't believe how much we
got.
>> I put about $40 in my pocket,
so it wouldn't be in the
bag,
just as a safety measure.
'Cause I figured, with
that,
I can definitely get a ride.
Treinta y cinco is a deal.
Treinta y...
>> Okay.
>> Yeah?
All right.
Let's go, guys.
Get the chicken!
Oh, you...
Stop the chicken!
( Rupert laughing )
We're pretty well fit
for the jungle right now.
I think we're...
we're definitely ready to
go
all-out for the next 40 days.
>> Seeing the flag, I'm
thinking, "I can't believe I'm
here.
This is the coolest thing
that's ever happened to me in
my
entire life."
I think that should be
the first big celebration,
the sheer excitement.
There was none of that.
What do you guys think?
>> Want to get everybody here so
we can say what we're going
to
do.
>> I got off the boat
last.
I walked up, and already
people were talking about,
"Where do we want to put camp?"
Blah, blah, blah.
I was, like, "Man, we're here!
"Let's jump up and down.
Let's give some hugs.
Let's do something."
There's none of that.
>> Someone get down there,
we'll scout out the area.
>> You know, we...
>> Get the fire going.
And the heavier people
can,
uh, can move the stuff,
move the cargo.
I was in game mode.
I wanted to get it done.
The words "Sunrise is going
down quickly" came in my
head.
I knew that we needed
to act fast.
I'd say we have
more room down there,
but if you guys want to all,
as a group, go run down
there?
You want to go walk out real
quick, so we can just get
the fire done like that?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's go running.
We don't have a lot of
time.
Whoo!
>> Osten was running up
and
down, looking for the perfect
spot to put the camp.
Osten's a big dude.
I mean, he's got, like,
muscles out to yay,
and, uh, I've been noticing
them
the whole time.
Because he-he lets you
know
he has muscles,
lets you know,
"Hey, I am strong."
I'm like, okay.
>> We can cut a couple of these
branches down.
These will kind of, like,
protect us from the...
from the rain a little bit.
You want to start the
fire,
and I'll start bringing stuff
over here?
>> Okay.
>> Lillian in her scout
uniform
was interesting, to say the
least.
I was completely thrown off-
kilter when I saw that.
I didn't know what the hell was
going on or was it a joke
or what was going on.
I was just confused.
>> Here, I'll blow on it.
>> My troop back home would
kick
my butt knowing I'm using a
candle.
It's real hard to take off
this scout hat.
It's real hard not to be
the scoutmaster here.
Oh, baby.
>> Good job.
>> Oh, baby.
Team effort here, girl.
>> Yeah.
>> If we build the shelter
like this, into the rock,
lean it up against the
rock.
You want to do that?
A lot less work.
>> There's this big shale
rock wall, and we think
there's this great bamboo post
just naturally lying
around,
and we're like,
"This is the best."
( grunting )
>> Oh, my goodness!
>> We made sure we had
somewhat of a shelter.
It was a... a lean-to.
( laughs )
But... oh, well.
You can only do so much
in that amount of time.
( cheering )
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> All right, guys.
>> Some rice, baby.
>> Don't waste the food.
>> It's home sweet home.
>> I think that's it.
>> Are you all right, guys?
Come on in.
We're all here.
We're going to have
the time of our life,
and at the same time we're
going to kick some butt.
>> Yeah!
>> Great, great, great.
>> First things first,
let's get a shelter built.
If we build a shelter,
like,
here, we can go around the tree.
>> This would be cool.
>> Yeah, this would be, right
here.
We're going to build
something over this way.
>> A shelter.
>> Yeah, like a little
shelter.
>> The shelter could go from
here to here, easily.
>> Burton, as well as, um,
myself, you know, off the
start,
we started getting
everything going.
We were just a little more
strong personalities,
a little more physical,
you know, mentally, as
well.
>> So what's the priority?
Bamboo or firewood, do you
think?
>> Both.
>> I was surprised at how
quickly we all worked
together.
I mean, we didn't know who we
were, what your name was
yet.
And, um, within a matter
of probably ten minutes,
we all sort of spread out and
it worked out pretty well.
>> One of the first items
on our to-do list
when we got here
was build a shelter.
And we did that.
Actually, it looked
pretty good.
>> Yay!
>> You know what we need?
A little bit bigger
firewood.
>> Bigger firewood?
>> We will pretty soon.
>> I was really tired,
I mean, just exhausted.
It was like, "for the love of
God."
I mean, I just wanted
to breathe for a second.
I was like,
"Does anybody have water?"
>> Here we go.
>> Burton opened up a
coconut,
and he shared the coconut milk
with only Shawn and
Michelle.
I gave Christa the look and I
said, "Did they offer you
any coconut milk?"
And she was like,
"No, and I wanted some."
>> Ah, refreshing.
>> Over the other side,
actually. Yeah.
>> Shawn and Burton are a little
out there in their
leadership.
>> It's a waste to just have it
lying underneath like
that.
It's not doing anything.
>> Put it the other way.
>> I have a better idea.
>> I just think they need
to be a little careful of that,
because they've already
alienated some people.
>> I love when people
with a beard, it's like, it
catches anything that
falls.
( laughter )
>> Shawn is being a pain
in the butt.
We're a strong little
team,
but the dynamic duo there that
are posturing for the lead
role
need to be a little more
careful, because they're
going
to make everybody hate them.
>> There's the other tree.
After making the shelter,
we went to go get water.
Water well, big tree.
The map says, "Go up a
trail
and to the right."
>> There it is.
>> We got water.
>> It's about a quarter of
a
mile to our water.
It's not that bad.
However, that's where
every single mosquito
on this planet lives.
Every one of them.
Holy mosquito city.
>> They are having parties
all
over me.
>> We didn't get any, uh,
bug
oil?
>> Oh, my God.
I'm getting attacked.
>> I am getting eaten
alive.
Every single one of us.
It's worse than I have
ever, ever, ever seen.
We got to get out of here.
God, these bastards
are everywhere.
>> Oh, you're just...
>> Mine's, like, the
craziest.
Oh, my God, you're not too great
yourself.
>> We were getting torn up
pretty bad.
I'm the least out of anyone.
That's it.
That's all I got.
Shawn?
(laughs)
He looks like the moon,
except in reverse.
>> There's not much water.
>> We're out of water?
>> We've gone through it, a
lot.
We only brought, like, 18.
>> How much of that do we
have
left?
I don't think we should
be drinking any more,
unless we go find some
and boil some...
>> Yeah, I think we...
>> We need to go find some.
>> I think water's going
to be real important.
>> Okay.
>> So what is... what is your
sense of water supply?
What-what are your
instincts on this?
>> I don't know.
I mean I, I...
I was looking for something
that, you know, followed
us up into something,
like animals would.
>> Yeah.
>> We saw some running
water,
and, uh, looked pretty orange,
it looked rusty.
It was not the kind of water
you'd want to drink,
even if you boiled it 42 hours.
>> Stagnant water like that
has
a bunch of diseases in it.
>> Yeah, that's pretty...
>> Looks like beer.
>> We meandered throughout
this
beach trying to guesstimate
where the water may or may
not
be, which was just a crucial
mistake.
Water's essential.
You need that.
The... the heat, the humidity,
your body's evaporating
fluids
constantly.
They need to be
replenished,
or you'll dehydrate
and you'll be going home.
And I don't want
to go home right now.
( clattering )
>> Uh-oh.
>> What was that?
>> Rocks and something
falling.
>> No.
>> Huh?
>> Yeah, it was.
From up... right up here.
>> The rocks falling from
the
cliff, um, that just didn't
work out at all.
Because we think it's going
to get worse,
especially if it starts to rain.
>> Ow!
Something bit my ass!
( laughing )
>> Are you serious?
>> I am!
( laughing )
>> What the hell is it?
( screaming laughter )
It felt like a crab!
What is that?
I have a feeling it was a
crab.
Oh, now, how am
I going to sleep?
As far as the little hermit
crabs, we think that we're
living in their home, pretty
much, because they were
just
crawling all over us, and they
pinch.
And there were, I mean,
literally dozens of them
crawling through there.
Why don't we just build
a shelter that's in the...
the middle of a ring of
fire?
And then no crabs can get to us.
>> My mistake not lifting
the shelter off the ground.
I'm sorry.
>> Whoa, whoa.
We got a snake!
>> Are you kidding?!
( laughter )
>> That's not a snake, it's a
frond.
>> Osten thought there was a
snake, but it was a palm
frond
that kept curling and moving.
And he freakin'...
he's pushing people out
of there, and we're
laughing.
>> Holy mackerel.
>> Oh, my God...
>> I could have swore it
was, like, slithering.
It kept coming down.
If I see something
or feel something, I
automatically go right
into...
freak-out mode,
and I don't know why.
Every time.
It-it just never fails.
I, honest to God, thought I saw
a snake.
I'm not, I'm not even lying...
>> I, honest to God,
believe
you.
>> It's hilarious--
we call him "Scary Mary,"
because he's never really
been
in a jungle environment.
Any little thing...
and if it touches his toe,
he leaps out of the air
and just shrieks.
( rumbling )
( gasps )
>> How close was that?
>> Was that a rock?
>> That was a rock.
>> Damn.
>> All right.
Let's do a toast.
To new friends, good friends
and nobody going home
anytime soon.
>> Whoo!
>> Yay!
( light applause )
>> I was big on getting the
booze yesterday.
We ended up trading a pair
of mismatched shoes
for some jugs of wine.
And that was a big deal to
me.
Oh, good golly.
>> We didn't get any
light,
we didn't get any soap...
>> But we need booze.
>> We got booze.
>> We got booze and
shelter.
What else do you need?
>> I don't know if it's
moonshine, wine, or just grain
alcohol, but we crack it
open
and taste it, it's the best-
tasting stuff we've ever
had.
That's good stuff, huh?
>> Oh, God, yeah.
>> That is really good.
>> Man, if you guys were
17,
you'd so be naked.
>> Like at the 7-11.
The wah-wah...
>> Jon, he reminds me of my
boys
who I mentor who just pop off
stupid stuff.
You know, talk about getting
some honey, or... smoking
something, drinking something.
>> Where are the teenage
girls?
Everyone laughs at all my jokes.
I knew going in that was
going
to be a huge bonus for me.
Because I'm not very
strong,
and I... I don't profess to be.
However, I'm a funny guy.
Trish, the dish!
You piss her off,
she be a bitch.
>> Jon is a goofball.
You can kind of get
the whole group laughing
and get it together.
I mean, which is great,
because we definitely need that
out here.
But I think at times,
he's a little obnoxious.
Anybody want this?
>> Yeah, I...
>> Yeah.
I'm going crazy!
>> He's out of control.
>> ( bleep ) you, man,
( bleep ) you!
>> I really can't stand
him.
He talks too much crap--
all night long, cursing.
He thinks it's cute,
but it isn't.
It gets old.
It's already old.
>> Whoo!
A girl in Vegas ( bleep ).
( laughter )
Hey.
>> Pass the bottle before you
drop it.
>> It's so sick, it was
( bleep ).
( laughs )
>> I don't think
this is ever going to dry.
Sleeping last night soaking
wet
really sucked.
Home would be so nice.
We did not purchase
any clothes in the
village.
We didn't think it was necessary
at the time.
>> Hey, girlie.
>> Out of all the things
that could happen,
I never thought that this
would be one of them, to just
have whatever you had on
and
that was it.
Man, I got to cut
these damn pants off.
( giggles )
I'm wearing my fancy,
my dress jeans.
Suckers were thick and hard and
heavy.
Them pants killed my crotch
where nice wet denim rubs
for a day and a half
and just starts eating
that skin away.
>> I do not want to wear
my sneakers today.
I want them to just dry
for once, just once.
>> Yeah.
>> A lot of us were pretty
miserable, but it was
like,
"Wait a second."
There's really a lot of
stuff
that you can do with just a
few pieces of clothing.
I can cut that seam right there
and make it a top and tie
it.
>> That could be a really
good top for you,
actually.
>> I can't tell you
how much better this
feels.
This wet thing has been
draping on me for days
now.
>> I can walk in these.
>> Finally making some
shorts.
>> Want me to cut it?
>> I'm wearing a nice
Armani
suit, but I had no choice--
they just had to come off.
Yeah, baby.
Beautiful.
( laughing )
>> As shorts, they dry in
half
the time, but I saved the
bottoms, 'cause I'm planning
on
making them into convertible
pants for the night.
>> We can get two skirts
out of this, and the bottom
part
will be big enough for you.
>> Okay.
Definitely.
My dress was falling
apart,
so we decided to go ahead
and improvise.
>> All right, chop her up.
We had a little fashion
club
meeting and took apart her
dress...
>> That is...
>> Oh, that is a skirt.
You hold this.
I want to put this on me
now.
>> Half of her dress is now
a skirt for Michelle...
and the other half is a skirt
for Blackbeard.
>> What do you think?
( all laughing )
>> My God, my thighs
feel so much better.
I got the little teasing
and laughing with the
girls
as we made it and I put it on
and I looked really silly.
It's done.
I'm wearing a dress.
I'm never gonna put
them pants back on.
>> Hey, you guys want to go
get some water?
>> Yeah...
>> Aren't we gonna look
and check our mail?
>> I thought we were gonna
all look for water first.
>> The biggest thing
that we need is water.
They say we'll go later for
the
water.
Personally...
we need to do it now.
Water well...
Oh, shut up.
Water well!
>> There's a water well
thing right on the map.
>> We were looking everywhere
for the water source,
not thinking, "Oh, let's look at
the map."
Water well is on our map.
>> Oh!
>> Nicely done.
>> Not just a pretty face.
>> Looked at the map, found
"Water well," so it
was exciting because we'd been
needing water for so long.
This is our boat.
>> It's a trail.
>> So, it's back here.
>> So... So we should just
follow that trail on back there.
>> Yeah, let's go get
water.
>> Why didn't we check the map
earlier?
That's what makes me angry.
>> Well, we were so busy
with
everything.
>> I know.
We need to kick ass
on that shelter.
Here's one of these bad boys.
>> Actually yesterday, we
built
a half A-frame up against a
shale wall.
It's actually pretty funny,
because I think
the shale wall was the home
to about 300 hermit crabs,
which paid us a visit
in the middle of the
night.
So, I thought we should
probably move our shelter,
so we're doing a little
penthouse suite here.
It's actually going
to have a floor.
We don't want to be
on the floor anymore,
so... where the crabs can get
us.
>> One of the biggest things in
my troop is we tuck our
shirts
in.
We look like a Scout,
we act like a Scout.
>> Yeah.
>> And here I'm running around
with my blouse open...
>> You know...
>> My shirt tied at the
waist.
( laughing )
I'm gonna come home and
they are going to razz me.
>> They're going to
critique
you.
>> Ooh, baby.
>> Lillian, I think I'm her,
probably her best friend
at the moment.
She kind of looks at the
other
girls as trying to be cute
and pretty and stuff.
And, uh, an-and me,
me and her go off
and have a good time
and talk and stuff.
( Lillian gasps )
>> Damn!
( screaming )
>> Yes!
>> Oh! You are wonderful!
>> We did it.
>> Oh! Oh!
Oh, how cool are you?
The one person who befriended
me with sincere friendship
was Ryan Shoulders.
Ryan's a good kid.
>> Yeah, I wish this stuff
was drinkable already.
>> I got an idea.
We ain't going to tell
them
where it's at.
>> I was just thinking
that.
( snoring )
>> I'm a very active
person.
I don't like to sit around
doing absolutely nothing,
and we had this spear gun,
and I looked around, I was
like,
"Hey, guys, I think
I'm gonna go out."
>> Have you used it before?
>> Oh, yeah.
Shawn went with me, and we went
out and we were swimming
around
and got into this
huge mess of fish
just all over the place.
>> Burton had the spear at
first, then next thing
I know, he cocks it...
And, all of a sudden,
we got a fish.
( tribe cheering )
>> All right!
Nice work, guys.
>> You know, he's going to
be
tasty.
>> Yeah. He's a good fish.
>> He's going to be very tasty.
>> I'm so excited that,
you
know, all right, this thing
works; we can do this.
>> That is awesome.
>> Mmm.
>> It feels great to be able
to catch food, but I knew
that one fish just wasn't
going to be enough,
so I took the spear.
So, I start catching fish.
Oh, I got lunch!
>> Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
>> After I got that,
I thought, "Okay, some more.
Some more."
>> Is that a catfish?
( women whooping )
>> I was thrilled.
I've never seen
a saltwater catfish.
I didn't know they made
such an animal.
>> You got another one?
>> Uh-huh.
>> He's going out again?
>> He's going to hurt himself.
>> Hey, Rupert.
Good job on those fish, man.
>> One, two, three, four,
five.
Three more.
>> Man, I hate to see
Rupert
out there.
Geez.
>> Wow, you're getting burned
on your shoulders, Rupert.
>> You look like you're
kind of getting red.
>> I got to the point
where I thought I was
going
to get eight of them.
Everybody was going
to get their own fish.
I didn't get eight,
but we got us fish.
>> You know what?
>> That's the best one
you caught, right there.
>> That one is.
>> No, the other one.
>> This guy?
I know if I could have
caught
more of these...
>> No, not that one, the
other one.
That one.
>> That one's a good one.
>> That's the best.
>> Rupert's definitely
a huge asset.
I mean, he worked his ass off,
but he was beat.
I mean, it took him hours to
recover from that.
>> Man, you are red.
>> I... I am burning up.
I had a great day.
I don't know if I can
keep up the workload
that I'm putting on
myself,
but that's what I told myself
I was going to do.
I'm coming out here
to be the caretaker.
I'm trying to make these people
believe that there is
no way you can get along without
me, and I think I'm doing
it.
>> Compliments to the catcher
today.
>> Absolutely.
>> Everyone did great.
>> Everybody.
>> There's mail.
>> Dude, it's our first
mail.
I guess, let's bring
it back and show them.
>> Great.
We have tree mail!
>> We got tree mail!
>> Mail, fools.
>> Whoo!
Read it out loud.
>> Read it out loud.
>> It's on.
>> Here we go. Here we go.
>>"You finally arrived
and so now it's on.
"Your first challenge is a
test
of your brains and your brawn.
"Like pirates of old,
it's the treasure you thirst.
But no booty will be had
if you're voted out first."
>> You know what booty that
is.
( all laughing )
>> Hey, I was thinking
for this challenge, seriously,
the challenge probably
won't
last very long.
So, if we just focus
for whatever, 15, 20 minutes...
>> The very first moment
Andrew gave the presence
of a leader, nobody
challenged
it.
>> Should we maybe...
>> Everything, everything...
>> ...appoint a leader?
Someone that just calls the
shots, so we don't get
stuck
fighting?
It makes no difference
to me who it is, but...
>> We need you.
>> Yeah, Andrew.
>> I made a suggestion
just
because I knew I didn't want
to be the leader, uh, but I
knew
that we needed somebody,
so we appointed Andrew
ahead of time as our leader
before the challenge.
>> Let's do it now, then.
Let's go out there.
>> The Morgan Tribe, I think,
is very ready for the
challenge.
Biggest concern from my
standpoint, from our tribe
is,
uh, Osten was having difficulty
with his shorts
last couple of days,
staying up.
The crack of his bottom
kept showing, and we said,
during any activity
against the other tribe,
if his shorts go down,
Ryan and I told him
that, uh, we're a team,
we're a family, and we
won't
make him embarrassed by being
nude, so, we'll, uh, do
the
same.
>> PROBST: Come on in,
guys!
Everybody good?
Let's get to today's
challenge.
One of the things
the pirates had to do
with all the loot that they
plundered is protect it.
So, that often meant moving
from one island to another,
and,
in the process, they would have
to transport their
artillery.
That's what you guys
are going to do today.
You're going to transport
the cannons behind you
through a series of obstacles
along a jungle course.
First, you're going to take
apart your cannon
and get it through two fences
blocking the path.
Next, you'll hit the rock
garden, where you'll have
to
clear a path to move your cannon
forward to the third
obstacle,
where you're going to have to
push, pull and drag your
cannon
through a mud pit blocked by
wooden barriers.
Finally, it's a race along
the shoreline to the
finish.
One person will carry the tribe
flag.
One person will carry the torch.
First tribe to reach the
finish
line with all eight members and
their cannon intact wins
immunity.
Want to get a look
at the immunity idol?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The most
valuable
thing in your 39 days is this
right here.
>> Yeah!
( applause )
Okay.
Big enough stakes.
Win this challenge, you're here
three more days, you are
safe.
Lose, somebody from your tribe
will be the first person
voted out at Tribal Council.
Give you a couple of minutes
to
strategize.
Wait for my "go."
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go!
( indistinct voices )
>> Go! Go!
>> Move it, move it, move it!
>> Come on.
We're right behind them.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Drake out to an early
lead.
>> We've got to take this apart.
That's the only thing...
>> Apart!
>> PROBST: Guys, you're going
to
have to take apart your cannons
to get it through the
fence.
>> Just push it.
Pull the cart all the way
up.
>> Watch your feet!
This thing's going to
fall.
>> Watch your feet!
Break it up!
>> PROBST: All wheels are
gonna
have to come off to get through
there.
Once everybody's through, you
can move through the other
one.
Let's go, Morgan!
You're falling behind.
>> Here we go.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Lift ya up.
>> Okay, let's go.
>> Ho-Hold on. Hold on.
Hold back!
( indistinct shouts )
All right!
Go!
>> PROBST: Drake through first,
still in the lead.
>> Walk it. Walk it.
>> Okay.
>> Let's rock and roll.
>> Go!
>> Get that log! Get that log!
>> Okay.
This?
We got to move this.
>> All the rocks?
Dude, we can't move
all those rocks.
>> Yeah.
>> We're not gonna get...
( indistinct voices )
>> PROBST: Let's go, Drake!
Got Morgan on your heels.
Ryan and Osten talking strategy.
>> My shorts?
( indistinct voices )
>> PROBST: What are you
guys
doing?
Osten, you are a first,
my man-- a totally nude
challenge.
We have two naked Morgan
members, and they are not
the guys anybody wants to see.
>> They better hope they
don't
lose their weenies out here.
>> Move some rocks, jerks!
>> PROBST: Great.
Now Andrew's naked.
>> Let's go, guys!
>> PROBST: Game is back
on!
You got a long way
left, guys.
It's going to be a great race.
( indistinct voices )
>> Run around and clear it!
>> PROBST: Drake still in
the
lead-- still controlling
the pace.
>> Go! Go! Go!
>> Go!
>> If you guys can
get out of the way
( indistinct shouts )
>> Push it! Push it!
>> Right, right, left, left!
>> Look out.
>> Go right ahead.
>> Good.
Come on, guys, push. Push.
( groaning )
( indistinct voices )
( grunting )
Watch out! Watch out. Watch out.
Come through. Come
through.
>> Let's go, let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
>> PROBST: Let's go, Morgan!
Keep it up!
( indistinct shouts )
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Through the flags!
Through the flags!
The cannons are heavy, guys.
They are going to
drag in the sand.
You're gonna have to
work hard to make it to
the finish.
Let's go, Drake!
Don't waste this lead!
Drake is bogged down.
>> Come on, we can do it!
We're beating 'em.
>> Come on, pull!
Watch out, guys!
>> Come on, Morgan!
>> PROBST: Keep going!
Morgan's taken the lead!
>> Push, push, push.
Come on, Morgan!
( indistinct shouting )
>> PROBST: It's a sprint to
the
finish!
First tribe across
with all eight members
and their cannon together
wins immunity.
Now Morgan's bogged down.
Here comes Drake,
back in the lead!
Down to the finish!
Got to get
through here!
Through here, Jon!
Through here!
( indistinct shouting )
>> Get up! Push!
( yelling )
>> Get up, get up!
Get up!
( indistinct shouts )
>> PROBST: Drake wins
immunity!
Oh, my God.
Drake!
>> And we didn't even
have to get naked!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Drake!
>> Here we go!
( cheering )
Wins immunity.
Congratulations.
>> ( chanting ): Drake! Drake!
Drake! Drake! Drake!
Drake!
( cheering )
>> Sweet!
>> PROBST: Morgan, great
effort,
down to the end.
Unfortunately, it wasn't
enough.
Next time I see you,
it'll be Tribal Council.
Somebody's going home.
You have the night
to think about it.
>> Drake!
>> I think it looks so pretty on
there.
>> When they passed us...
>> Oh, dude...
>> ...I was ready to puke and
cry.
>> When we won that challenge,
we beat them not on brute
strength alone, but we beat
them on... on, basically,
in
my opinion, willpower.
They gave up.
And we didn't.
You know, we almost did, but
we
didn't.
And I think that's why
we made it to the end.
Dude, just too many
naked men behind us.
>> At the immunity
challenge,
I looked back and I saw one guy
with his junk just hanging
out
just like, you know,
nobody's business.
And that...
I was like, "Whoa!
I shouldn't be looking."
Their asses were in my
face.
>> Yeah!
So just say you looked.
>> Did you enjoy it?
>> I wasn't impressed.
I don't know what
was going on with them.
I wish their ding-a-lings
got stuck on a vine
or I don't know.
That was just stupid.
>> Do you know why the boys
took their panties off?
>> Dude, I have no idea.
>> Did you enjoy it?
>> When I turned around
and saw them idiots
bouncing around naked
in the mud and the muck
and the stickers and the thorns,
( chuckles ): it was
hilarious.
>> The coolest thing is,
thank God, we don't
have to send anyone home
tonight.
>> Yeah.
>>'Cause that would have
sucked.
>> Exactly right.
>> You know, that sucked,
any way you look at it.
We lost by about a foot.
We learn from it.
We move on, and we kick
their butt the next time.
And we remember how cocky
they were when they won.
All right?
>> Hey, guys.
We were just talking
and just thinking about...
>> You were?
What were you talking
about?
>> We were...
we were just thinking
about,
obviously, tonight.
>> You ladies saw what we
saw.
>> What did you see?
>> I saw our friend Ryan,
who's back at the camp,
just quit about a third
of the way in.
And every time I looked
over, he said, "What?"
It's like...
>> With Lilly, I mean,
she works hard when it comes
to
the fire and the water,
but we all can do fire and
water.
>> I think it's a big
mistake
if we expect other challenges
to be less strenuous.
>> Yeah!
>> So, the question is,
is Lilly up for that
or are we better off
with the limp noodle, Ryan?
>> But I don't fit in
here with the girls.
I don't fit in with the
boys.
>> Hang in there.
This thing changes every
day.
>> I took the challenge loss,
I think, the hardest,
because I feel like I am...
going to be encouraged to
leave.
( chuckles )
>> When your torch goes
out,
then give up.
>> All right.
>>'Cause it's over then.
( Lillian sighs )
>> But not until then.
>> I think my teammates like
me,
but someone has to go.
>> Do you want to try and
crack
one of them?
>> No one else has said
"Side
with me," other than Nicole.
>> Uh... Lill, I think
Tijuana is the person
that I think needs to
be taken care of quickly.
And, at this point, while
we're
still building the shelter,
we don't want to get
rid of any of the guys.
( chuckles )
Truth... truth be told,
I like all of them.
>> Nicole came to me, and...
she wants to get rid of
Tijuana.
You know, okay.
You know, why?
Well, this is...
this is what went on for
me.
Nicole comes to me, she tells
me, "Let's get rid of
Tijuana."
>> What?
That's a hell of a
strategy.
She says she's bugging her...
da da da.
"Will you help me?"
And I'm going, geez, you
know,
that didn't sound too cool.
>> Lilly...
I had... had some conversations
with her, and I believe
everything she says.
I don't think she has
a dishonest bone in her body.
Lill said Nicole came to
her
and said, "Will you
form an alliance
"with me to vote off...
>> Are you serious?
>> Tijua..." Wait, wait.
...to vote off Tijuana."
>> Nicole approached Lilly
because Tijuana was
apparently
being too bossy and was
annoying Nicole.
>> Are you serious?
>> They're saying, too...
>> She told me that Lill went
to her.
So she blamed it on Lill,
and it's Nicole that's doing
it.
>> Lill has not denied it.
Lill just tells you the
truth.
We're just trying to figure out
who said what to whom
and...
and whether Nicole can be
trusted.
>> Ooh! Ooh!
That pisses me off.
What I had to do
is find out is Nicole
lying.
Was she really trying to put me
on the cutting block?
I really believe that she was.
I think Lill...
I just don't think she has a
reason to lie.
>> All I want to know is who's
backstabbing me.
I don't have any...
>> Nobody's backstabbing
you.
Nobody's voting for you.
>> Somebody obviously is.
>> How?
I did talk to Lillian
to get rid of Tijuana,
but word got out of that
because Lill's freaked out that
she's getting voted off
tonight,
so she's telling everybody.
I set myself up
in a really bad position,
telling some truths,
telling some half-truths
and trying to get things
to go my way.
She approached me.
>> Somebody's lying.
It's either Lill or it's
you.
And that's not a good thing,
because who knows when
you're
going to be talked about or
lied about?
>> I was getting along
with Nicole there
for a little while,
which I still am.
But, you know, now I don't know
if I can trust her.
>> Okay.
>> You've made me feel
very
uncomfortable in this situation.
>> But you're not
listening.
He told me.
I didn't create it.
He told me, so I came
directly to you.
I didn't want to make a
judgment call.
>> And then you would go and...
I wanted to ask you.
>> If you don't trust me,
and if you think I'm out
to get people...
>> I want to trust you.
>> ...why would you want
to have an alliance?
>> That's why I'm asking
you.
As far as Nicole, I think it is
enemy status.
It's gotten to that point.
I can't trust her.
So, yeah, she's definitely an
enemy.
She came right off the bat
trying to take me down.
For what purposes?
For what?
>> The people that I
think are at risk?
>> You're hungry, aren't you?
>> Skinny Ryan.
I don't...
he just hasn't been
pulling his weight at camp
or at the challenge.
>> Well, we gotta go.
>> Nicole, with the high
drama
today, she's been labeled in
some people's eyes as
being
dishonest.
And, uh, so her neck's
on the line, because we don't
know if we can trust her.
And Lilly, is her neck
on the chopping block?
Yeah, she's
definitely, uh, a
contender
to be voted out tonight.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: I want you to grab a
torch and approach the
flame.
Dip your torch in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council, because
fire represents life on
the
island and in this game.
When your fire is gone,
so are you.
Put your torches back in
their
slot and have a seat.
Welcome to your first
Tribal Council,
not the place you want to
be.
But, uh, before we get
to the vote, let's talk
about
the challenge, the reason you
guys are here tonight.
It's one thing to get naked
for no apparent reason and
win,
but it's another thing entirely
to have three guys walking
around naked and lose a
challenge.
Any regrets about that?
>> Absolutely not.
Not a regret.
What's in the past
is in the past.
We did it and we move on,
period.
>> PROBST: So, how has it
been,
Ryan?
How are the first three
days
of getting along with these
people that you didn't
know?
The first three days has
been good for me.
I... I get along with everybody.
Everybody's really cool,
everybody's really helpful,
but... food, I could care
less
about.
The water aspect, I'm
struggling
a little bit.
>> PROBST: Andrew, has
water
been the toughest part?
>> No. Uh...
I'm very...
I'm hydrated.
For me, it's the sleep.
I haven't had more
than 45 minutes sleep
the last three nights.
>> PROBST: Why?
>> Well, we built a
fashionable
hut, and we put a floor down.
And the poles were uneven,
so that didn't work very well.
So, we didn't quite get
the job done.
>> PROBST: Lill, you're a
scoutmaster, right?
I mean, the...
it's not just decorative.
>> No. It... it's
hard-earned.
It's 11 years of being
scoutmaster of, um, troop
in Cincinnati, Ohio.
>> PROBST: And has that
served
you well out here?
>> It has served me well.
It has also given me patience.
Uh, you can't work with
a bunch of young children
without having patience,
so...
I'm patient.
>> PROBST: Let's talk
about
friendships.
How about you, Nicole?
Friendships out here?
Um, I think I have some
social
friendships, but I don't...
I think it's too early to
trust
anybody.
I've already seen several
sides
of a few people.
Just when questioned
or when threatened,
I've seen people that are
normally very cheerful
and very positive
turn very defensive.
Um, having me feel funny,
that
was from the very first day.
>> PROBST: Has anybody
emerged
as a leader that... that you
guys are looking to now to
make decisions?
Lill?
>> Um...
Andrew is our leader.
We've elected him as a team,
and he's done an excellent
job.
He's willing to listen
to each one of us, and I
like
that in leadership.
>> PROBST: Andrew, as the
leader, anybody here not
pulling their weight?
>> Young Ryan.
At the challenge,
we were side by side, I'm
pulling the left-hand
side,
and he didn't wake up
and show me the passion
that
we needed.
So... yeah, I don't think he
was
pulling his weight.
>> PROBST: So, Ryan, first
three
days, you been pulling your
weight?
>> I know there has been some
talk among some people
that I didn't give my 110%
at the, uh, at the
immunity
challenge.
And I thought I was giving
120%.
If they see me otherwise,
that's fine.
We'll go on.
>> PROBST: Okay.
It is time to vote.
Nicole, you're up first.
>> Ryan S., I'm voting for
you
because you're the only person
I know other people are
planning
to vote for.
>> Nicole, you stabbed me
in
the back.
Fortunately, I found out
and I was able to save myself.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally
the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will
be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Nicole.
Ryan S.
One vote Ryan, one vote Nicole.
Nicole.
Two votes Nicole, one vote Ryan.
Three votes Nicole.
Nicole.
That's four votes Nicole.
The first person voted out
of the Pearl Islands,
Nicole.
You need to bring me your
torch.
Nicole, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Judging from tonight's
Tribal Council, it's clear
a couple of you certainly
thought that could have
been
your torch.
So, maybe the thing
to be learned is that you are
not out of this game until
your torch is snuffed.
Keep that in your head
over the next 36 days.
You can always save
yourself.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: At Drake, life is good
until Shawn causes Rupert
to lose his cool.
>> That's why I wanted to be
the
only one... who did that.
( yells )
And a member of the Morgan
Tribe wants to quit.
>> We don't need people just
walking around, "I
don't...
I want to go home."
It's a real morale killer
for the tribe.
>> I knew going in that
my biggest weakness
was going to be keeping
my mouth shut.
When I have an opinion
about somebody,
I just can't seem
to keep it in.
Um, based on past
experiences
in my life,
it doesn't surprise me
that I'm sitting here.
Um, I knew I'd either be
the first person off
or the person that won.
So, it was one of the toughest
things I've ever done.
And, even with a million
dollars at stake,
I still had to say what I
thought when I thought it.
And that's exactly
what did me in.
I sort of shot myself
in the foot by trying to
make
an alliance early on to get rid
of someone that was just
annoying me, um, which I see
now in hindsight is probably
not
the best way to play the game.