>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor:
Morgan, never able to catch
their own fish...
>> These make it better.
>> Nicely done!
>> PROBST: ...enjoyed the skills
of Rupert, their temporary tribe
mate.
>> Probably the smartest thing
this tribe ever did was get
ahold of Rupert.
>> PROBST: At Drake, with Rupert
away from camp, his loyalty was
questioned.
>> I'm afraid he's giving away
too much information about us
and not realizing it.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, with Rupert still on
board, Morgan claimed victory.
Morgan wins reward!
Rupert then returned to Drake,
where he was greeted with open
arms.
We welcome back this guy.
Morgan returned to camp in high
spirits-- with rain ponchos, a
cooking pot, and a chance to get
clean.
At the immunity challenge,
Rupert arrived with a new
friend...
>> This is Balboa.
>> PROBST: ...and Darrah kept
the seafood smoothie down,
leading Morgan to their third
straight win.
Before Tribal Council,
Michelle made a last-minute
plea to stay on the island.
I can't trust Shawn further
than I could throw him.
>> PROBST: But it wasn't enough,
and at Drake's second Tribal
Council, they voted Michelle
out of the Pearl Islands.
Michelle, the tribe has spoken.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
(thunder rumbles)
>> I thought Michelle left
with a lot of class.
>> She did.
She's a very good girl.
And it's too bad she's not on
our tribe anymore.
My first Tribal Council sucked.
I was mad and I was tired.
I was pissed off.
I didn't want to be there.
>> I tell you, Jeff was pretty
direct with his questions
tonight, wasn't he?
>> He was trying to get to the
bottom of stuff.
>> He didn't want to hear no
sugarcoating, nothing.
>> We were brutally honest this
time.
And I am sorry that I, I...
if I offended anybody in any of
my answers.
I hope I didn't.
>> No. No. Not at all.
>> Good.
They still do not see that we
gave Morgan some great momentum.
They don't see that.
I can't believe I wrote
Michelle's name down instead of
Shawn.
Should have been Shawn.
(sighs)
For awhile, everybody knew
a Drake was going to win this.
Now, there is question.
You all right, Balboa?
Oh, you feel awful cold.
You're not...
You didn't make it through the
night, buddy.
(sighs)
This morning, I went and
checked on Balboa.
He was dead.
So sorry, buddy.
It's a hard world.
>> How's Balboa doing?
>> He's dead.
>> Is he really?
>> They want to use him for
bait, so I'm burying him.
>> He died last night?
>> Yeah, he's gone.
>> That's so sad.
>> Rupert was a little upset.
You know, he gets really
attached to funny little things
and the snake was one of them.
I don't know why he's so worried
about a little snake he found
in the water, but, you know,
who knows? That's Rupert.
(squawking)
>> Hey, hey, hey.
You don't need to be doing that.
Oh, you want to challenge me?
(chuckles)
Come on.
(squawks)
He's trying to get our flag.
Move it.
Hey, buddy.
You're out of here.
>> There's a pelican
that just came by camp, and
Ryno has a soft spot for
animals, which is great.
So, Ryno starts petting it,
making it feel good, and he's
just trying to help it out.
So, it was pretty funny.
Did you give her a name yet?
>> His name's Pelican Pete.
He's our mascot for a little
while.
(squawks)
>> Your friend is waiting
outside for you.
>> Oh, yeah, here he comes.
>> He's really coming and
following you.
(laughing)
Osten's going to be highly
upset.
You want to come in?
Come on.
(laughing)
Osten, don't do that!
Be nice.
Just see what he does.
He's not going to get up here.
>> Why would you want this
thing in here?
I'm being dead serious.
I'm, like, I would get
the machete and chop this
thing's head right the ... off.
I'm not playing around.
(squawking)
I'm going to get the machete
right now.
I'm not playing around.
>> He wants to sit on your lap.
>> I am not kidding.
(laughing)
Here he comes.
>> I think it's hilarious that
Osten is scared of every little
thing.
I mean, he's such a big guy, you
would think that, you know, he
wouldn't be scared of anything,
but, you know, he's scared of
every little bug.
>> Come on, buddy.
Let's go.
You're not welcome.
Come on.
>> I don't like animals.
I been bit by a couple
animals, and the next animal
that bites me will die.
I have no problem chopping that
thing's head straight off.
Just go sit down and stop ...
with your blade.
You don't need to do that.
Not chopping anything's ... head
off unless we're going to eat
it.
We're not eating this one.
Come on, buddy.
Come on.
>> Ryno's just trying to
help out a poor old pelican
and O.T.'s just being an ass.
There's no other way to look
at it.
He's just being an ass,
sharpening machete.
That's the dumbest thing I've
ever seen.
In fact, I was embarrassed by
that.
>> Sit down, though.
I don't... I don't need you to
irritate me right now.
I believe Osten was afraid of
it.
He was, he was pissing me off.
I mean, if you're afraid of
the jungle and you're afraid
of the sea and you're afraid
of birds... You know what?
Don't even come out here.
(squawks)
All right, Pete.
I'll see you later, buddy.
>> If we have a free day today,
I'm gonna gather logs and
we're tearing our floor apart
and getting it six inches,
eight inches off the ground.
>> Rupert felt that if we could
elevate the bamboo off the
ground, even a few inches,
that that would stop the
biting at night.
>> We want to keep away from the
sand as high as we can.
>> Even though most of us did
not understand or agree that
this was going to help anything,
we would do anything to stop the
biting.
>> I really think that just
to raise it an inch or two with
bamboo is almost a waste of
energy and time.
We might as well wait till
tomorrow.
>> All the ... off, we're doing
it today.
>> Damn straight.
>> So, everybody starts taking
the shelter apart and what
happened?
Shawn told Jon, "Well, I think
this is all a waste of time.
"I don't think we should be
wasting our energy doing all of
this."
>> I just don't think it's going
to make much of a difference to
raise it this much.
'Cause that bamboo is like...
two inches high, not even.
>> Shawn kept looking for
excuses why not to help
and Jon's, like, had it up to
here with him.
>> Rupe, you don't think we
could just slide, like, lift up
sections and slide the logs
under?
>> Jon. Stop.
Where you going, Jon?
>> I know, but I'm getting tired
just watching everyone just
watching.
>> Yeah, but, you know, you're
making, uh, ten times more work.
>> No we're not!
We're doing...
It's ten times more work to talk
about it for a .... hour.
I'll have all these out by the
time everyone's ... done just
looking at it.
>> Jon, honestly, relax, bro.
>> Damn it, dude!
You do more not to do work
than doing work!
>> What are you talking about,
Jon?
Relax. We're working here.
>> No, you're just, you're not--
>> Are we on a time basis?
>> I could give a ...!
Dude, don't tell me to...
Just do it and I will relax!
>> Jon, chill your ... head, all
right?
>> Oh, my God.
You're ... ridiculous, dude.
Don't even go there.
>> I just asked you to just pull
those out.
>> Just shut up!
Just shut up, okay? Shut up.
How about that one?
Try that one.
>> I'll ... shut up the day you
start ... working.
>> You know what, Jon, just shut
up, all right?!
>> God! You still can't do it!
>> Just shut up.
>> I'll ... walk away just for
you to ... do it!
>> Walk away.
>> I will!
>> Good.
Ridiculous.
>> No, what's ... ridiculous is
not doing anything!
That's ... ridiculous!
>> You see us here, Jon?
Relax! Okay?
>> I'm glad Jon put him in his
place.
And after that, what happened?
Shawn practically put
the whole shelter together.
Maybe Shawn should get a clue
that he's not anybody's buddy
here.
That he needs to get
whatever has to happen done.
He needs to make sure we win
the challenge... or he's going
home.
And that's it.
>> Sea mail.
>> That's a cool pouch.
>> A cannonball.
>> What's it say?
>> "Batten down the hatches,
it's time to have a blast.
Ready, aim, fire!
Who'll be standing last?
Will your tribe fall short or
will you go too far?
Your stomach will thank you.
It's the tastiest reward by
far."
>> Food, baby!
(cheering)
>> You know, I think we're
feeling vulnerable going into
this next challenge.
We really want to get our
momentum back.
And we've lost three
challenges in a row.
Today's a new day, we're a
strong tribe.
We're totally united.
All we have to do is get our
strategy back for the next two
challenges, and just kick ass
and just make it happen.
>> I know.
We're going to go kick some
Morgan ass.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Take a spot on your mat.
Morgan, getting your first
look at the new Drake tribe.
Michelle voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Drake now down to six members.
Numbers are evening up.
You guys ready for today's
reward challenge?
Let's get to it.
For today's challenge, in
classic pirate style you will
fire a cannon.
One tribe member at a time
will come up, you will load
the cannon, you will aim the
cannon, and, using fire, you
will light the cannon.
Your goal: knock out one of the
other tribe's targets.
First tribe to knock out all
four targets wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, hell yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: First part of today's
reward... is a grill, utensils.
Make it a little easier,
anyway.
Put this over your fire, put
your fish or whatever meat you
have.
And I'm sure the fish is
starting to get a little bland,
so, a few spices.
Got some chili pepper, got some
parsley, salt and pepper, little
bit of everything.
Should, if you know what you're
doing, spice it up a little bit.
And if you're getting tired of
fish... nice big lobster.
>> Oh, lobster.
That's exactly what I said.
>> PROBST: And if you're just
tired of seafood altogether...
here's a little steak.
(gasps and laughter)
>> PROBST: In addition,
Morgan, should you win,
second piece to your buried
treasure.
Also, the winning tribe gets to
loot one item from the losing
tribe.
Give you a minute for strategy.
Wait for my "Go."
Here we go, guys.
First two up: Jon and Savage.
First tribe to knock out the
other tribe's four targets
wins surf n' turf.
Savage gets loaded.
Jon gets loaded.
Now, the critical phase:
aiming the cannon.
You have ropes you can use.
You also can tilt or lower.
Andrew likes his already.
>> What do you think?
>> I think that's it.
>> PROBST: All right, Savage,
which one are you going for?
>> Front right.
>> PROBST: Front right.
Get your fire.
Morgan's first shot.
Ready?
Fire.
(tribe groans)
Wow!
>> PROBST: A little high and had
a little English on it.
Drake's first shot, Jon the
guinea pig.
Which one?
Going for the orange one.
Here we go.
Ready?
Fire.
(groaning)
Close.
Next two, come on up.
Ryno, it's loaded.
Sandra going to load in.
Ryno, get your fire.
Ready?
Fire.
Boom, he connects.
Morgan on the board with one.
Sandra, get your fire.
Ready?
Fire.
Ooh, nicely done!
We're 1-1.
Next two, come on down.
T. gets loaded up.
Grab your fire.
Ready?
Fire.
(groans)
>> PROBST: Too high.
Ready?
Fire.
(cheering)
>> Whoo!
>> Wasn't the one I was aiming
for, but...
>> PROBST: Drake takes the lead,
2-1.
Next two, come on down.
Osten and Rupert squaring off
once again.
Ready?
Fire.
>> Yes!
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: And he does.
Rupert, grab your fire.
Ready?
Fire.
He nails it!
Next two, come on down.
Drake, one target away from
surf n' turf.
Darrah gets loaded.
Shawn gets loaded.
All right, Darrah.
Grab your fire.
Ready?
Fire.
(cheering)
>> PROBST: And Darrah connects.
We're tied up 3-3.
Shawn can win it with this.
Ready?
Fire.
(groaning)
>> Just a tad over.
>> PROBST: A little low and to
the right.
Next two, come on down.
Savage and Christa.
Here's where things stand:
We're tied at 3-3.
Morgan will shoot first.
You connect, you have all
four.
Drake still gets their
last shot.
Savage tweaking.
A lot at stake on these two
shots.
Christa eyeballing.
Both tribes happy?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Andrew...
Ready? Fire.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: A miss.
(Drake clapping)
Christa, if you hit the one
remaining target: surf and
turf is going home with Drake.
Ready?
Fire.
(cheering)
>> PROBST: And she does!
Drake wins reward!
>> Drake! Drake! Drake!
>> PROBST: Drake!
Beef, lobster, spices.
You guys will take this home
with you.
Tomorrow morning,
you'll be sending somebody
over to Morgan to loot one
item.
Enjoy-- bon apetit.
(cheering)
>> Oh, look at these steaks,
man!
>> PROBST: Morgan.
Grab your tribe flag and head
on back to camp.
(Drake cheering)
>> Surf and turf.
Steak and lobster and spices!
>> Look at these little fellas
right here.
And they ain't little.
Look at our spices...
Rosemary. Garlic sauce.
Wait, wait.
>> The piece de resistance:
>> Beef. We got beef.
>> I mean, it was just like a
dream come true.
And when we came back here,
everyone seasoned up their own
meat and made their own steaks
and it was unbelievable.
I think the lobsters are done.
For sure.
>> God, they look so good,
Shawn.
Oh, my God.
>> It felt good coming
home with all that stuff.
We tore it up.
We cooked the lobster first.
>> Oh, man!
That's cooked perfectly.
>> I can't believe after all
this, we still got steak, guys.
>> Then, came around to the
steak.
>> This is so good, you guys.
>> And I just picked it up
off the grill and I just ate
it off the fork.
It was so delicious.
It was the greatest steak I've
ever had.
This is the bomb.
>> You're going to have to get
up in a few minutes and go loot.
Okay?
>> Okay. I'll get up.
>> You want to wake up.
>> I'm about to go lootin'
and takin' some of that old
pirate's booty.
I'm going to have fun today.
Their morale is pretty low as a
result of losing the reward
challenge.
Uh, so, I... I plan on taking
that morale and jumping on it,
just up and down so it's
absolutely nothing come
immunity time.
That's the goal.
>> Who's that?
>> Jon.
>> Is it?
>> It's too early for me.
(laughs)
>> He's an irritant.
And he's rude.
>> Okay, T, unclench your fists.
(laughs)
>> What's up, Big Jon?
What's up?
>> Little Jon from Drake
came to our camp to raid it.
He was a lot more humble than
he usually is.
He looked like he put his
diplomat hat on, remembered some
of his people skills and he...
he wasn't as cocky or as
arrogant.
So what are your thoughts
today, Big Jon?
Everyone voted we have to take
your pot, uh, as a strategic
move, in case you come after our
pot.
>> I thought you were coming
after the shower.
>> Nah. I... you know what?
I would love to wash my
hair before I go.
>> Then Little Jon indicated
nothing would make him happier
than to have some shampoo to
wash his hair.
Gave him some shampoo,
a diplomatic gesture on our
part.
>> Awesome.
Have you guys noticed
I've been a little nicer at
challenges?
>> We don't mind talking smack,
but it hurts when you lose six
straight challenges.
>> Oh.
>> If we were winning those
challenges, talking smack
doesn't bother me.
It just...
>> Well, technically, seven.
We threw the seventh one
just to get Burton out.
Like, I mean, did you notice
that I... I moved my guys out
of the way? But, anyway...
I'll be right back.
>> Throwing the challenge, him.
>> Seven is what he said.
>> Him.
>> Who said that?
>> He said he... they threw the
challenge for that piece...
chess piece, as if they
weren't trying.
>> Yeah, right.
>> The whole time.
>> He screwed up, majorly.
>> He claims he threw the
Chess-Checker Water Challenge.
I think that's just nonsense and
I think it's bad sportsmanship
for him, little bastard, to
indicate that we didn't fair and
square win that challenge.
So, I don't think they did throw
it.
But just for that little pissant
to take that away from us, it's
ridiculous.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Bye.
>> You know, he came here
to ruffle some feathers and he
definitely did.
Hey, say "hey" to Rupert for us.
>> I will.
>> And it concerned me from an
immunity standpoint, because
the most critical one coming up
today, that he's causing
dissension among the ranks.
And let the games begin.
Let's take the gloves off and
let's see what they're made of.
Let's have some fun.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
What's going on, Rupert?
>> ( laughs ): Play time.
>> PROBST: What's up, T?
>> Hey.
>> PROBST: Christa, getting more
bug bites.
>> I don't know what happened to
me last night.
I guess I just have some new
freckles that have developed.
It's cool.
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first.
Immunity... back up for grabs.
Okay, today's immunity challenge
will require strategy and
endurance.
Three tribe members from each
tribe will have a wooden pole
across their shoulders.
Each round, weight will be added
to those poles until you cannot
take it any longer.
That's the endurance portion.
But the decision of which
tribe member gets the weight
added to their shoulders will
be made by only two members from
the opposing tribe.
That's the strategy.
Once you can't hold the weight
any longer, drop the pole,
you're out of the game.
Last person left standing wins
immunity for their tribe.
Drake, because you have one
extra member, you're sitting
somebody out.
Sandra's sitting out.
All right.
Wait for my "Go."
All right, guys.
We'll be working in 20-pound
increments.
Each bag weighs ten pounds.
You'll put two bags on each
person.
Drake, where you putting your
first 20 pounds?
>> Osten.
>> PROBST: Morgan, where you
putting your first 20?
>> Rupert.
>> PROBST: Rupert. All right.
Grab your bags.
Put them on.
Let them go.
Next 20 pounds.
Morgan, where's it going?
>> Rupert.
>> Osten.
>> PROBST: Where's the next 20
going-- Morgan?
>> Rupert.
>> PROBST: Savage.
All right.
Drake dividing it up a little.
Rupert going to take another
20 and Savage getting his
first 20.
Morgan, who's your next 20?
>> Rupert.
>> PROBST: Rupert.
>> Savage.
>> PROBST: Savage.
Remember, you have a
limited amount of weight,
600 pounds, to allocate.
Rupert at 80 pounds, Osten at 40
pounds, Savage at 40 pounds.
Morgan?
>> Rupert.
>> PROBST: Rupert again.
>> Osten.
>> PROBST: Osten.
Now it looks like we're going
with the same strategy on both
tribes.
Rupert's at 140 pounds,
Osten's at a hundred pounds,
Savage at 40.
Osten, how you feeling?
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Let's put some more
weight on.
>> I hate doing this, Rupe.
(exhales)
>> PROBST: Once again, Rupert
and Osten showing down.
(growls)
>> It ain't lasting.
>> Keep it up, Osten.
You got it.
>> You got it, Osten.
>> PROBST: Rupert at 200 pounds
now.
Making a risky move by taking
his hands off that bar.
>> He's in pain, too, Rupert.
>> Keep focus, Osten.
>> You looking good, Rupert.
>> He's trembling.
>> PROBST: Osten at 160, plus
that bar is another 15, plus the
pain you feel in the back of
your neck.
Both men struggling.
It's going to come down to will.
>> He's done!
>> He's out.
>> PROBST: And like that, Osten
is out.
>> Stay in, Rupe.
>> PROBST: Take a seat, Osten.
>> It's all right, Osten.
(groans)
>> PROBST: Put some more weight.
>> Rupert.
>> PROBST: Rupert.
>> Savage.
>> PROBST: Savage.
(grunts)
>> PROBST: Rupert has lost his
pole.
>> All right, good job, Rupe.
Good job.
>> PROBST: The strategy worked
for both tribes, heavy up on the
strongest guy.
Both strong guys are out.
Have a seat on your crate, Rupe.
All right, let's give somebody
else some weight.
>> Savage.
>> Shawn.
>> PROBST: Drake going to heavy
up on Savage.
Morgan spreading the weight
around.
That's going to start getting
heavy.
That's a lot of weight
and an uncomfortable bar on
the back of your neck.
>> Got to break one of them.
>> O.T. was saying Shawn first.
>> PROBST: Let's add some
weight.
>> Shawn.
>> Savage.
>> We're breaking him
right here.
>> PROBST: Let's add some
weight.
>> Shawn.
>> Ryno.
>> PROBST: Ryno finally in the
game with 20 pounds.
Shawn's carrying 120, Savage
still holding strong at 160.
(indistinct encouragement)
>> Hang in there, Shawn.
>> PROBST: Shawn now at 140,
still 20 pounds less than
Savage.
>> Give him some more.
>> No, don't need to-- Ryno.
>> He's going to break.
>> He's done.
>> PROBST: Savage has somehow
managed to hang in for a long
time at 160 pounds.
>> You got it, Shawn.
This contest was made for you.
>> PROBST: And with that, Shawn
is out at 140 pounds.
Savage, still holding strong at
160, a weight he has been at
twice as long as anybody else.
>> Come on, Morgan!
>> PROBST: Let's add some
weight.
It is down to Christa versus two
strong Morgan guys.
>> Hang in there, Christa.
>> PROBST: Very impressive.
Christa now at the same weight
Osten dropped out at, 160.
Same weight Andrew's been at
for 15 minutes.
Ryno at 140.
This is where you have to
fight through the pain or give
in.
>> It's just too much on the
human body.
>> PROBST: Let's add some
weight.
>> Savage.
>> PROBST: Drake changing up.
Trish doesn't like the
decision.
Big strategic move and it was
one that was not agreed on.
>> She's going to fall.
Right here.
Right here, she's falling.
>> Stay in there.
Stay in there.
>> PROBST: Got to fight through
it.
She can't do it.
Morgan wins immunity!
>> It's okay, mama.
>> You did your best.
You had 160 pounds.
>> PROBST: Morgan, it's going
back home with you again.
You should give that to Savage.
Well earned.
>> Give it a kiss.
>> PROBST: You got tears in your
eyes-- you all right?
Feel good?
(Andrew sniffles)
Drake, I know you weren't
planning on going to Tribal
Council, but you are.
Somebody's going home and, after
tonight, we'll be even:
five-five.
You have this afternoon to think
about that vote.
Head on back to camp.
>> I should have stood up there
longer, guys.
That's all I got to say.
We wouldn't have this problem.
>> Everybody did as much as they
could.
>> That was the worst,
pitifulest-ass performance I've
ever seen.
He deserves to go home, if
nothing else, for that.
I am very irritated with
Shawn.
I want him off my island and
out of my adventure.
We may just go fishing.
>> All I know is one person has
a hell of a lot of power right
now.
>> Yep.
>> It's not right.
I mean, just so much power.
>> Yep.
>> It's like, he could pretty
much do whatever he wants to,
frankly, and we're all sort of
following along.
>> Jon and Trish feel insecure
about Rupert's power within the
tribe, because Rupert is the man
in charge here.
>> You know, I love Rupe, but
there's something that is just
not feeling right to me about
this whole thing.
>> Agreed.
>> You know, if anybody could
jump to Morgan and survive, it
would be Rupert.
With us, he could go all the
way, and with them, he could go
all the way.
I mean, what do you guys think?
I-I-I don't... you know...
>> Christa won't go for it.
>> Well, we don't have...
we don't need Christa.
>> We're not telling her.
>> We're not telling.
>> We're not telling Christa.
All we need... all we need is,
uh, us three and Shawn.
Shawn will say yes in a
heartbeat.
>> What do you think?
>> What are the ramifications if
we do?
>> Food.
>> For a million dollars, can
you starve for 19 days?
>> Yes.
>> So it's a done deal?
>> I guess so.
It has to be.
It's the smartest way we can
play this game right now.
>> The more we talked
about it and the more we
fleshed it out, the better I
felt, the better Jon felt, and
the better Sandra felt.
Jon didn't want to tell Christa,
because we don't need her vote.
Shawn-- we're going to tell him
at the last minute that his
neck has been saved.
This is the biggest shock of
all-- that we have all come to
this conclusion on Rupert.
Tonight, it's going to be a
really big surprise.
Rupert's going to be the one
gone and not Shawn.
>> Oh, man, this is crazy now.
First it was Shawn.
Now we're down to Rupert.
>> Rupert would never do us
wrong.
I trust him.
>> I'd rather keep the tribe
strong just a little while
longer.
>> Rupert.
>> Huh?
>> They're planning on getting
rid of you tonight.
They're not going to go with
Shawn.
They've changed.
Jon and Trish-- they want you
out.
>> I can't believe that Jon and
Trish are trying to get me out
before even the merge.
We do not even know when the
merge is going to be, and
they're trying to get me out.
Jon and Trish are going to
come try and sway you and get
them... you to vote me.
That's still only going to be
three votes.
>> Right.
>> And it'll be a tie.
>> Three against three.
>> So I should say yes.
>> You write Trish down.
>> Say yes to voting you...
>> Say yes to voting me.
>> And then write Trish.
>> Then write Trish down, and
Trish is out fo-four to two.
>> And then you and I are going
to take this one home?
>> Hell yeah.
>> I'm with you on that, baby.
>> I was pretty upset because I
thought I was going home.
Then I talked to Rupert,
and he found out that the plot
wasn't to get me off tonight,
but to get him off.
And he came running back here to
say, "It's you and me.
Let's get rid of Trish.
She's the bad apple."
So we'll see.
Wait, who's taking a ride?
Rupe? Rupert?
>> Yep.
>> Where'd that come from?
>> Had to do something.
There's no way anyone can go
against Rupert to the final two.
It'd be a landslide.
It'd be a freakin' K. O., man.
You got to do what you got to
do.
>> That is for sure.
In this game, you have to do
what you got to do.
>> Exactly, so I trust you more
than any of them, so...
>> If you don't do what you got
to do in this game, somebody
could take you for a ride.
>> Yep.
Everyone's really ready to
vote off Shawn, but Shawn's a
good ally for me.
Rupert?
Uh, good guy, but I'm not
signing my million dollar check
to him, so that's the way the
game's played.
>> Remember I said, "You look
out for my back, I'll look out
for yours"?
That's what we're doing.
Little do they know what's
really going to happen.
I think everyone is going to be
very shocked.
Everyone.
(chuckles)
>> PROBST: Well, judging by how
confident you guys act at
challenges and seeing that
today's immunity challenge was
physical, I know you were not
expecting to be here again
tonight.
Sandra?
>> Definitely not.
We were on full tummies.
Our motivation was up there.
We were like, "There's no way.
"They're dying "of hunger.
"They don't have it together.
There's no way we can get
beat. No way."
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's challenge.
Christa, you outlasted a lot of
people, including Morgan's
strongest guy, Osten.
You had as much weight as he did
when he dropped out.
>> The challenge was hard.
I... didn't think that I
actually could pull that much
weight, but, uh, I did.
And it sucked to drop it,
though.
>> PROBST: Rupert... I'd be
lying if I didn't say you looked
incredibly sad.
Your eyes are sunken.
Your smile is gone.
>> 'Cause I'm ready to cry.
>> PROBST: What's that?
>> I'm ready to cry.
>> PROBST: Why?
>> We shouldn't be here.
>> PROBST: So are you upset
about losing?
Are you upset about where the
tribe is?
>> I'm upset the way the tribe
has gone.
We started out so strong, and
now we are not.
And it's hard to pull everybody
together.
>> PROBST: Are you losing hope
that that can happen?
You can't lose hope.
You got to believe that you
can.
We'll lose one person tonight.
I hope it's not me.
And maybe then, we'll try and
build a stronger Drake tribe.
>> PROBST: Why would it be you
tonight?
>> I think my tribe sees me now
as unneeded.
They have gotten it in their
heads-- even though I'm trying
desperately to make them
believe there is no
certainties of a merge, there
is no certainties of anything
in this game-- that if I make it
to the end, they can't beat me.
Uh, if I make it to the merge,
I'll win a lot of the
immunities; they can't beat me.
Doesn't give a damn if I catch
them ten pounds of fish a day.
I know at least half my tribe
wants me gone.
>> PROBST: Trish, when you hear
a guy like this, who's been a
strong member of your tribe,
feel like half the tribe has
turned on him, what are your
thoughts?
>> I'm surprised to hear him say
that, to tell you the truth.
I didn't know he felt that way
at all.
So, to hear him talk like that,
you know, it's-it's, um... sad
to me.
I had no idea that that's the
way he felt.
>> PROBST: Is it hard for you to
vote somebody out tonight?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely.
It's really hard for me to vote
somebody out tonight.
>> PROBST: Sandra, how sure are
you that it's not you tonight?
>> Oh, I know it ain't me.
(laughing)
The person that's going home
today is the one that least
expects it.
It's the person that in the past
couple of days has been giving
so many different stories that
we don't know what the heck to
believe.
This person will be missed, but,
for the good of the tribe, this
person has got to go home.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: With that, it is
time to vote.
Christa, you're up.
>> (whispering): You stabbed us
all in the back.
You have no idea how to play
this game, but good try.
See you later.
>> Everybody's got a price,
everybody's got to pay, 'cause a
million dollar man always gets
his way.
>> I've always said you were a
snake from day one.
Um, you can't be trusted, so,
um, good-bye, adios.
>> Rupert, I'm voting you out
because I think you just have
too much power with the other
tribe, and it just seems to me
that you are straddling both
tribes.
>> I cannot believe that you
turned on me so quickly.
Everybody in my tribe tells me
that you want me out, and you
lie right to my face.
I can't take that.
>> You know what?
Game's over for you.
It's my game now, so good-bye.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote--
Trish.
Rupert.
That's two votes Trish, one
vote Rupert.
Rupert.
Two votes Rupert, two votes
Trish.
Three votes Trish.
The sixth person voted out of
the Pearl Islands-- Trish.
You need to bring me your
torch.
Trish, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, the one thing that came
out of tonight's Tribal Council
is that there are very
few things that are certain in
this game.
One thing that is certain-- this
tribe has been to Tribal Council
three times in a row.
You are now down to five
members, same as the Morgan
tribe.
21 days left.
It is anybody's game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> Who the hell voted for me?
>> I did.
>> You ... me!
Jonny Fairplay is Jonny
Pain-in-the-ass now to me.
>> PROBST: At Morgan...
>> O.T., this morning, he
checked out.
I could see in his eyes, he's
throwing in the towel again.
>> PROBST: And Morgan and Drake
are in for a big twist.
Your past has come back to
haunt you.
>> I didn't see this coming at
all, obviously.
But I always knew that anything
can happen.
And so, I really never took
anything for granted.
Hats off to the Drake Tribe.
I think you guys are all great.
I hope one of the Drakes end up
winning the million dollars.
Good for you guys, you kept a
secret, and that's the beauty
of this game-- you just never
know what's going to happen and
when it's going to happen.