>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor...
The Morgan Tribe was in a slump
after Osten asked to be voted
out.
>> He quit.
>> I think there's a big
difference between quitting
and pulling the trigger
and actually quitting.
>> PROBST: The Drake Tribe
searched for buried treasure
with the first piece
of their map, but came up
empty-handed.
>> Hopefully, get another piece
of the map today, so we can get
the next clue.
>> PROBST: After reward
challenge, the two tribes
battled for new bedding,
a piece of their treasure map
and a chance to loot
the losing tribe.
Go!
With the help
of Rupert's brute strength,
the Drakes stayed afloat
and won their fourth challenge
in a row.
(cheering)
Making matters worse for Morgan,
Lill lost the tribe's last
fishing hook.
>> Oh, I'm gone for good now.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, with Darrah and
Michelle hanging in the balance,
it came down to a test
of strength and will
between Rupert and Osten.
But Rupert held on and secured
another Drake victory.
(shouting)
At Tribal Council,
Morgan chose Darrah's strength
over the scoutmaster's work
ethic.
And Lill was voted out
of the tribe.
13 Are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
♪ ♪
>> This morning, we had a little
bit, uh, higher tides
'cause there's the storm
out at sea.
So, it kind of blew our
little fortress wall away.
It seems like, as the month
is going on,
the tides are getting
higher and higher.
So, the wall needs
to be bigger and bigger.
Otherwise, we're going
to need to move our shelter
somewhere else, and I really
don't want to do that.
Put the whole sand wall
right across here.
We need to just reinforce it.
We're in an uphill fight
and we have been ever since
we got here.
It's almost comical now.
>> Think about a double barrier,
so we got... you know, right
here the last wall of defense.
We are absolutely devastated.
Our morale is low.
We, at Tribal Council last
night, voted out Lill.
We definitely feel the impact
of her not being there.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Okay, it's ready?
>> Yeah.
>> Darrah and T are taking over
the, uh, water responsibilities.
I think it's us against
everything else out here,
against the surf,
against the mosquitoes,
against the crabs.
>> This is a crab that we found
under our bed.
>> They were trying to get us
last night... from underneath.
>> Against the fire ants,
everything.
>> Are those fire ants?
I think they are.
There's, like, a log
where they live
and they're being smoked out
and coming out
all over our camp.
>> We desperately need fish.
The, uh, coconut, rice
and beans,
I mean, it's sufficient for now,
but we really need
just that extra boost.
Also, from a morale standpoint,
it would be a huge victory
for us to actually catch a fish.
>> Jon, need any help?
>> I filled everyone
in on the status of...
of the jug all day.
>> Dude, I know, I...
>> And the day before.
>> Jon, I... I'm not...
>> You knew it had to be
done and you want to tell
everyone else it should have
been done, and... and you said
three hours ago,
then you could have done it.
So, then don't complain about
it.
>> I've been doing
everything else.
>> That's not my point.
Everyone else has been doing...
what are you saying?
>> I am, mad, because everyone
else...
>> Yeah, we took a rest
because it's hot today.
>> I know.
>> Are you trying to say you're
the only one who does
something around here?
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
>> So then, what's your problem?
>> I'm saying that a little more
help would be appreciated.
I've been working for three
hours.
This is the first time
I stopped working
to complain about it.
It's not a big deal.
That's the problem.
>> Okay.
>> You know, the mood today
has been really funky, I think.
It's been really weird.
You know, I think people
are getting testy,
and they're just
sort of, you know...
we've been out here for ten days
and the personalities are
starting to get to one
another a little bit.
And morale for some reason,
today, has been really off and
on, and I can't figure out why.
>> You hear what Shawn said
this morning that him and Burton
are always the first ones to
wake up and to do everything?
That's a bunch of baloney,
'cause they're rarely
the first ones up.
I woke up happy
until I heard that crap.
>> I think because, uh, we've
won so many challenges,
it's starting to get annoying.
Because we really want
somebody to leave.
Did you go to college, Shawn?
>> What's that?
>> Did you go to college?
>> Yes, I did.
>> Did you graduate?
How about yourself?
Did you graduate?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> There's definitely tension.
Christa's always had her
little issues with me,
and, you know, she's made
her little comments,
things that just get on my nerve
and I've just smiled right
through them and not said
anything back.
But, at the same time,
I take note of everything.
What you say is going
to come back to get you,
and in this case,
it's coming back to get her.
>> These guys that are here,
especially Shawn and Michelle
and Burton, I just don't
get along with them.
I don't feel the connection
with them.
I don't feel like I can
speak my mind like I normally
can.
And I'd rather have them
out of here.
>> Dude, just, whatever you do,
say no to crack.
(laughs)
Nothing, dude.
>> I'll kill you.
>> Some plumbers wear skirts.
>> I'll kill you!
>> Son of a bitch.
Snap your neck like
a damn chicken!
You know, I don't know,
I turned around and Burton's
pointing at my ass
and laughing at me
and just being an idiot.
You know, it's like high
school.
The... the pretty boy
jock-ass idiots all got
to pick on me.
>> Rupe.
>> Rupe. Rupe. Rupe.
You know, you're the prettiest
one in a skirt around here.
>> The whole time we've been
here, Shawn and Burton and
Michelle kind of cliqued up
right away, and, you know, I
don't know why they did that.
I can only assume
that the two guys thought
they were just so strong,
that there's no way they were
going to get voted off.
And, of course, Michelle's
adorable, and so they cliqued
right into her.
But I don't think they realize
that they alienated everybody
else in the tribe.
>> PROBST: Drake, here's your
first look at the new Morgan
Tribe minus another member.
Lill, voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
How you guys doing?
>> Great.
>> PROBST: Okay.
For today's reward challenge,
you're going to be
solving a puzzle.
There are 16 pieces to the
puzzle.
Eight are buried in the sand,
eight are floating in the water.
One tribe member at a time,
you're going to retrieve
a piece from either the water
or the sand in any order you
want.
Once you have all 16 pieces,
the entire tribe can then begin
to solve the puzzle.
First tribe to finish
the puzzle wins reward.
Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Got something a
little different this time.
To help you out
with your wardrobe,
old-fashioned sewing machine,
along with a sewing kit.
>> Make me a new dress.
>> PROBST: We've got all kinds
of material.
In addition, another piece
to the location
of your treasure chest.
For Drake, it would be your
third and final piece.
Morgan, it would be
your first piece.
Finally, the opportunity to loot
one item from the other tribe.
Worth playing for?
>> ALL: Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, Drake,
because you have three extra
members, you're sitting three
people out in this challenge.
Who are you sitting out?
Shawn, Michelle, Christa,
take a spot on the bench.
Wait for my "go."
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
Ryno and Burton
starting out the race.
Burton, with his first piece,
heading back in.
>> Way to go, Burton!
>> PROBST: Burton with the first
piece for Drake.
Sandra heading to the sand.
>> Dig like your name,
Sandra.
>> PROBST: Sandra gets the first
piece from the sand.
That's two for Drake.
Morgan with their first piece
of the puzzle.
Andrew Savage getting one
out of the sand.
We're tied up at two pieces.
Darrah ready with the mask.
Tijuana heads out instead,
showing a little booty.
>> Oh, nice.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Skirted man with
the third piece for Drake.
Trish digging for another one.
>> I can't find it!
>> T!
>> Come on, T!
>> PROBST: Jon with another
piece for Drake.
That's five for Drake.
Burton heads back out
into the water.
>> Burton!
>> PROBST: Tijuana having
trouble without the mask.
Burton with another
piece for Drake.
Sandra going to the beach.
Tijuana with a piece,
struggling to get back now.
>> That's okay.
>> PROBST: Rupert heading back
out for a swim.
That a way, Tijuana.
Drake with seven pieces,
Morgan at three.
Osten heading into the water.
Rupert with another piece
for Drake.
Jon with another piece
Burton back out into the water.
>> Put that mask on.
It's right below you.
>> I'm about to drown.
>> PROBST: Are you okay?
>> No!
>> PROBST: Hold on to the rope
right there.
>> I need help!
>> PROBST: Hey, who's the best
swimmer?
Go give him a hand.
>> I need help!
>> PROBST: Osten's in trouble.
Give him a hand, Andrew.
Osten, you're okay!
Hang on!
>> Rupert, go!
>> PROBST: Great teamwork,
Morgan.
Way to not quit.
Drake moving on
with their 12th piece.
Osten safe and sound,
back on shore.
Rupert with another piece for
Drake.
Ryno back in the water.
Let's go.
Trish looking for
the last piece in the beach.
She's still looking.
You guys are in it.
Savage going for a beach piece.
Trish still struggling.
Morgan still fighting.
Another piece for Morgan.
Darrah heading back out
in the water.
Darrah with another piece for
Morgan.
>> Back up!
>> PROBST: Tijuana digging for
a piece on the beach.
Trish going to use a stake
to try and find it.
Tijuana has another piece for
Morgan, fighting to get it out.
She has it.
Morgan closing the gap at nine.
Ryno back out in the water
for Morgan.
Trish finally has it.
Another piece for Drake.
That's 11 for Morgan.
Jon stumbling into the water.
Morgan with another piece.
That's 12 For Morgan.
Drake needs one more piece.
Burton going in for the last
piece in the water.
Morgan with two in the water
and two on the beach.
Darrah with her 13th piece.
Drake has all 16.
Flip them.
Start solving.
Osten going for the short beach.
That's 14.
>> Top of the head.
>> This is a corner.
Perfect!
That's perfect!
(shouting)
Ryno still fighting for Morgan.
>> Other way.
Other way!
>> PROBST: Drake wins reward!
(cheering)
Six challenges in a row.
>> Yeah!
(Drake members cheering)
>> Let's find out where the hell
that devil's fork is.
>> PROBST: Drake, another piece
to the location of
your buried treasure.
>> Great job!
>> PROBST: Your sewing machine
will be delivered.
>> Thank you.
>> Whoo!
>> ALL: Drake!
>> All right, let's see
where we're measuring today.
We'll do your waist?
>> Go underneath my hips.
>> You're gonna have a skirt,
too, Rupert?
>> Yes.
>> Let me move all the way
around.
It's a big belly to move around.
>> You could have made shorts.
>> I don't care, I just want
something to cover my ass.
>> I love the sewing machine.
We couldn't have gotten
a better reward,
and I think Rupert is awesome.
He's the only man that I know
that would wear a skirt
out in the middle of nowhere
just to be comfortable,
and he's the only man I know
that would start sewing away
and have no shame.
All he has
is pride in his skills,
and I think it's awesome
that he actually knows
how to make his own clothes.
>> Hey, look at this guy
over here, Mr. Sewer.
What you making?
>> A new dress.
>> Ooh, sexy, sexy.
You gonna have slots up the
side?
Beautiful work there.
When you're done, I got some
pants that need hemming.
>> Good for you.
You can get right on that.
>> Burton and Shawn never leave
Rupert alone about his skirt.
I mean, don't keep
talking about something
that keeps bothering somebody.
If you know it bothers somebody,
why don't you just shut up after
awhile?
>> Look at that, you tied a
string in there and everything,
huh?
>> It's like a muumuu.
>> That is awesome.
(laughter)
>> Oh, God.
>> How's that feel?
>> Much better, huh?
>> Much better.
I feel lots better.
>> All right, guys, listen up.
"The easiest road for you to
tread will be to walk up
"the old creek bed.
After that, there's searching
still.
"Take a left at the stump
and head up the hill."
Done that.
>> "Find the devil's fork
and your quest is complete.
"Go 15 paces due south
and it's under your feet."
>> We found it, baby!
(cheering)
I know where that is, baby.
>> So, after the last reward
challenge, we finally got our
third and final piece of our map
for the treasure chest,
and we were just bouncing off
the walls ready to find it.
>> I'm hoping there's candy
and maybe some canned juice
and peaches and pineapples
in there, I don't know.
Anything but rice-- if I see
one more grain of rice,
I'm gonna... I'll be upset.
I'm gonna go wild.
>> We talk about the treasure,
we dream about the treasure,
we fantasize about the treasure.
Like, I've had more, uh,
wet dreams about that...
that treasure than, uh...
than any girl in Playboy.
(chuckles)
>> Rupe, anything?
>> No.
>> I bet it's here.
It's got to be here.
It's out all by itself?
>> I don't know, that, to me,
looks like a fork out
in the open, to be honest.
>> Why is this not jumping out?
>> Look at this map.
Come back here and
look at this map.
>> We have not found it yet.
We're still back to the same
dilemma we've been in
the whole time, which is...
the directions say
"find the devil's fork."
The clues say "go 15 paces
due south."
The map shows going 15 paces
due north, but there's no
obvious "devil's fork" out here.
>> Does that look like
a devil's fork to you?
If you think of what's in here,
there's nothing else
as big and obtrusive as
that thing right there.
>> I'm buying that.
>> What?
>> What about over here?
>> It is really soft.
>> Feeling anything?
(gasps)
Is that it?
>> That seems like wood.
Dude, I think this might be it.
Look, there's metal, see?
>> Woo-hoo! Keep digging!
Keep digging!
>> I think I got it!
>> We got it!
>> I got it!
>> It's over here!
>> So, show me the devil's
fork.
>> It's right there.
>> Right there, baby.
>> At that big tree.
>> Look at it from the other
side.
>> Shawn, you're a god!
>> Yeah, baby!
>> We've won three challenges,
we've gotten three maps.
We searched this island
high and low, and here it was.
We were standing
on the freakin' treasure.
>> Barbecued potato chips!
>> Eight pair of pants.
>> Bacon cheeseburgers!
>> New underpants!
>> I'll be happier
when I see what's in there.
(grunting)
>> Hold on, dude.
Hold on.
(Rupert grunts)
There is a handle.
>> Where is the handle?
>> What if you can
just open the top?
Is it possible?
So, after trying and trying and
trying to bring the chest up,
they said, "Okay, the hell with
it, screw this.
Let's pop the chest open."
When they cleared away the
lock...
>> Just be careful with our key.
>> Don't break it.
>> ...and finally it popped
open.
>> Oh!
>> And, oh, my God.
A stench so awful.
Smelled like death.
>> Someone open this.
Should we lay out a blanket
and put everything...
Oh, God.
>> It smells horrible,
horrible.
>> They're moldy.
>> Everything's moldy and nasty.
>> They're all molded.
>> Hey, it's better
than nothing, you guys.
>> Oh, a bottle of something!
>> Yeah.
>> Candy!
>> Get the candy out!
Get the candy out.
>> I have to say the one thing
that put a smile on everyone's
face-- and thank God it was in
there, was this thing of
chocolates.
I mean, I don't...
I think we would have ripped
each other's heads off
if those chocolates weren't in
there, because that's how
disappointed we were.
>> Rupert, take a break.
Everybody sit back
and have chocolate.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I'm in heaven.
>> Oh, my God!
>> So, we open it up,
there were goblets,
candleholders, candles.
We got a lot of canned food.
There's sugar, there's honey.
>> Sugar!
>> Moldy beef jerky.
>> Some coffee beans,
there were some chocolates,
which made everyone
feel a lot better.
The treasure had leaked a little
bit, some of the stuff was wet,
and I wanted to say,
"You guys grow up.
You're being babies about it.
"We got something, and anything
is better than nothing."
>> The blankets smell like crap.
The hammock smells like crap.
The mosquito net smells like
crap.
I-I'd call it a ghetto
Christmas.
It's like asking for an
Incredible Hulk doll and... and
getting your sister's Ken doll
painted green.
It's just not the same thing.
>> It's a quick shot
to the other side here.
I've been through here.
It's a really thick, thick
jungle.
>> Then just walk along
the coastline...
>> Ryno and I are going to have
a go at fishing today
with the spear because we
lost all of our fish hooks.
So we decided to go on the other
side of the island.
The big map indicated some
dorsal fins, indicating sharks
or fish, so we thought,
since we haven't had any luck
around here, although we've
seen some fish, that we thought
the other side of the island
may have a multitude of fish.
We going the right way?
What do you think?
>> I don't know.
That looks like
an opening down there.
See where the light is?
>> Let's have a look.
Cool.
>> We're going to make it.
>> I can see the coast?
>> Yep.
>> There is looting this morning
for the Drake Tribe,
and they'll be coming over
to take another item
from the Morgan Tribe.
>> If they want to cripple us,
they'll take our pot.
They take our pot,
Morgan, as we know it,
is no longer, 'cause there's
no longer... we can't cook food,
we can't boil water,
we'll be dehydrated, end of
game.
>> I hate to do this.
>> Whatever.
>> I'm Trish.
>> Hi, Trish, I'm Tijuana.
Nice to meet you.
>> Hi, Tijuana.
>> Come on.
>> I feel so bad.
>> Yeah, whatever.
>> I really do.
>> How are you guys doing over
there?
>> We're doing okay.
Hi, you guys.
>> Hi.
>> I'm Trish.
>> I'm Darrah.
>> Nice to meet you.
How are you guys doing?
You making out okay?
>> Yeah. Our boys went to go
fishing.
>> Oh, they have?
Wow, yeah.
>> What?
Not any further down?
>> This is definitely
The Blair Witch Project.
>> All right.
It could be just
a little farther down.
>> Do you realize how dangerous
it is to not have water?
Yeah.
>> So what do you think you
guys are looking for?
>> Um...
This is the coolest shelter
you have.
>> Thank you.
Our tough men put that together.
>> It's nice.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, I guess what they want
is the lantern.
>> You guys are gonna take our
lantern?
>> I know. I hate it.
I was trying to talk them into,
like, not taking anything.
I was, like, so shot down, man.
I was, like, just no way.
>> We're relieved they didn't
take our pot, 'cause that's our
only pot, and that's kind of
what we were wanting them to
take was the lantern.
That's what we were wanting
them to take last time.
We probably ruined it
by putting cooking oil in it,
so it's probably not going to
work.
>> Is that it?
Why is this side so choppy?
I thought the other side was
supposed to be calmer.
>> That's where I think we are.
>> Oh, yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> This is not accurate though.
>> Clearly this is not the big
cove as indicated on the map.
It seems to me we went due east,
pretty much a straight line.
We should have hit the cove dead
on and, uh...
we didn't, so it's major league
frustrating for us.
We need fish very, very badly.
I mean, we don't have any
energy.
We don't have any water.
Phenomenally frustrating.
>> Both me and Savage are done.
I mean, we're pretty much
burned-out.
I don't even know how long
we've been out here, but, uh...
I think the tribe's going
to be a little bit upset
that we don't, uh...
have anything for them.
>> So, last night, I woke up
in the middle of the night.
Couldn't sleep.
I saw that Rupert was up.
I'd been meaning to talk to him.
I was a little hesitant
because he's so gung-ho
on the whole Drake Tribe.
I've been running every
single scenario through my head.
>> Yeah?
>> Because you and I are
screwed.
You and I are the two toughest
of the 16.
>> Right.
>> As soon as there's a merge,
the strongest people are going
to be the first people to go.
I know right now Rupert and
myself are the biggest threats
in our tribe.
Between Jon, Trish and Sandra,
if they do really start putting
it together, hell, yeah, they
should get rid of us now.
We don't need to win any more
immunities.
>> Right.
>> At some point, we should
lose.
We can do it, but we have to get
rid of Christa, and we have
to get rid of Trish, and we have
to do it soon.
Can you do that?
If to keep us... to keep this
tribe together, yeah.
Heck, yeah, I can.
>> That's what I wanted to hear.
>> When Burt comes to me and
says, "We're going to get rid of
some of our Drakes..."
As soon as he said that,
I wanted to smack him
and say, you know, "Traitor."
If this was a pirate culture,
he'd already be dead.
>> If we go to immunity,
and we don't win,
and we get rid of Christa,
we're in a good position.
But, God, we've got to get rid
of Christa.
So this conversation is between
you and me.
>> Oh, most definitely.
>> And, as long as no one else
knows, we can run the game.
>> Right.
>> Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Sea mail.
Sea mail who?
"Familiar with the game of
checkers?
"Familiar with the game
of chess?
"Heard of professional
wrestling?
>> Uh-oh.
>> "Combined make a worthy
test."
>> "Formulating strategies,
"take some time to think.
To avoid the next
"Tribal Council, send your
opponent in the drink."
>> In the water, homes.
>> Full contact chess, man.
>> Someone has to be dunked?
>> We are, as a group, thinking
about throwing the challenge.
The alliance that I'm with,
we're all ready to get
Christa out right now.
And, therefore, are willing to
back off from the challenge,
and not give it 100%.
>> My alliance is interested
in throwing the challenge
to cut out a little bit of
cancer in our tribe: namely,
Burton.
In that, I can sit out
on a challenge.
I already told them that,
if I'm in a challenge,
there's no way in hell
that I would lose.
Throwing a challenge
is the stupidest thing
that Drake could ever do.
But will I stand back
and let them do it?
Yes, if that's what they want
to do.
>> PROBST: Welcome, Drake,
Morgan.
First things first.
Burton, I need the immunity
idol.
Get that up here.
Immunity back up for grabs.
Okay. For today's immunity
challenge, once again we look
to the world of pirates.
Back in the day,
when they ruled the seas,
it was only a matter of time
before they wanted
to board your ship.
And the only way to stop them
from doing that was to engage
in battle.
Each tribe member will move one
space at a time across
the platform.
Your goal: get to the other
side.
If you are blocked by another
tribe member,
you will have to engage
in a showdown.
When two people decide
to show down, it will be
a battle of strength
and balance.
First person to hit the water
is out, has to swim back to the
beginning, start again.
The winner moves forward
one space.
The first tribe to get all their
tribe members to the other side
wins immunity.
And, along with immunity,
a little something else we'll
save for after the challenge.
All right, Drake, because you
have three extra members,
you're sitting three people out.
You cannot sit the same people
out in back-to-back challenges.
Who's sitting out?
Rupert, Trish, Burton,
you stay in the boat.
Everybody else strategize,
wait for my "go."
At stake: immunity, and a
surprise reward for after the
challenge.
Drake, you won the coin toss.
Who's moving first?
Sandra makes the first move.
First move for Morgan.
Osten on the course.
Shawn.
Ryno.
Michelle moving out
onto the course.
Andrew makes his first move.
A lot of showdowns lining up.
T on the course now,
with a smile on her face
and ready to take somebody on.
Jon saves himself for last.
Darrah on the board.
We have all ten
tribe members out.
Now it's going to get good.
Morgan.
Osten challenges Michelle.
Here's what's going to happen.
I'm going to tell you
to put one foot in the white,
and then, when you both have a
foot, I'm going to say, "Go."
Once I say, "Go," it's on.
First person in the water
is out,
and goes back to the start.
Here we go.
Foot in the white.
Go.
(screams)
Michelle in.
Osten doesn't even get wet,
moves forward.
Michelle goes back to the start.
Got another showdown:
Ryno and N.Y.C.
Go!
Ryno in.
Shawn doesn't get wet.
Shawn moves forward.
Ryno back to the start.
Morgan, got another showdown.
Osten challenges Jon.
Go!
Jon takes a bath.
Osten moves forward.
That is one for Morgan.
Take a spot in the Morgan boat.
Andrew challenges Michelle.
Go!
Oh.
Close.
Waged a good battle,
but Michelle's first in the
water, she's out.
Andrew moves into the last spot,
and, with that, it's two Morgan,
nothing Drake.
We have another challenge:
Shawn taking on T.
Go!
Yeah!
T first in.
Gave it an effort.
Very good.
T back to the start.
That's one for Drake.
>> Good job, Shawn.
>> PROBST: So, I got to ask
at this point:
Obviously, it's a strong
physical battle and your two...
two of your strongest guys
chose to sit out.
Why come?
>> Wasn't my choice.
>> PROBST: Wasn't your choice?
You guys have a rotation
that doesn't change.
All right, that works.
Drake.
Michelle challenges another
showdown.
Ryno moves into the spot.
That's three Morgan members,
one Drake member.
Morgan giving T the chance
to take Jon in.
Jon first in the water!
Take a swim back.
Christa in the water.
Back to the start.
Darrah moves forward.
Darrah, you move forward.
Sandra takes her last move.
And, with that,
Sandra's in for Drake.
T moves to her last spot.
Morgan has their
fourth member across.
Michelle is in,
and off the course.
Darrah, the only remaining
member of Morgan, needs to get
in.
Here's where we're at.
Morgan at four, Drake at three.
First tribe to get
all members in wins immunity.
Drake... and a little something
else.
Morgan... just a matter of
playing it out now.
Drake.
Darrah, make the only move you
can-- the last move.
And, with that, Darrah moves in.
Morgan wins their first
challenge.
Morgan wins immunity!
Morgan finally on the board.
Congratulations.
All right, Morgan,
immunity for your tribe,
and a little something else.
I shall read the note.
"Choose one tribe member
from the opposing tribe
to come live with you
until the next challenge."
Here's what that means.
You are going to choose
a tribe member from Drake
right now.
They will leave with you right
now.
They will not go to Tribal
Council tomorrow night.
They cannot be voted out.
They will participate with you
in the next reward challenge and
share in that reward if you win.
Who's it going to be, Savage?
>> Rupert.
>> PROBST: Rupert, for the next
short while you are now going
to be living with Morgan.
Out of the boat, into the Morgan
boat.
>> Rupert, all right, baby!
>> We love you, Rupert.
>> It's all good, baby.
>> It's all good.
>> We love you, Rupert.
>> Love you guys.
>> Hey, it'll only be temporary.
>> PROBST: And a nice welcome
from Ryno.
I think Morgan likes you,
Rupert.
Here you are, Darrah.
Morgan, congratulations.
Head back to camp.
Drake... I will see you
at Tribal Council.
We have a lot to talk about.
Head out, guys.
>> It was a little scary that
Rupert went away with the other
tribe.
It was kind of a shocker.
And, uh, I got a little nervous
after this immunity challenge.
I'm thinking that I could be
the next to go.
>> Come on, it's me and you, the
macho man versus the little man.
>> I'm thinking that maybe Jon
may go with Michelle, Shawn and
Burton, but I highly doubt it.
So, I'm going to keep positive
thinking and continue to think
that he's with Trish, Sandra
and I, even though Rupert's
gone.
And, uh, hopefully it will be
Burton to go instead of me.
>> The way I see it... the way
I see it, Jon, to be honest
with you, there's four of us
right here.
I don't give a ... who they
vote for because there's no
previous votes cast.
Sandra can go ... me.
When... when we hear four votes
for Christa, whatever the other
three votes are for, you know
that one of those votes were
cast by those three people right
there.
And when they come back here,
they're going to know they just
sunk their own ship.
>> Jon claims he's fully onboard
and, I've got to be honest, all
the actions and all the things
that Jon has said have been
very consistent over the past
week about getting Christa
off.
>> You're a little nervous, but
once you've voted, uh, Christa
gone, you know, show your
loyalty, we're all cool.
We'll carry you to the end.
That's... Burton's just worried
right now, but he's going to be
going like, "Oh, okay.
I... I understand."
>> There is a lot of scheming
going on.
It's very funny.
Some of the things that Jon
comes back and tells, uh, Trish
and Sandra and I.
>> Who do they think we're going
to vote off-- Michelle?
Tonight?!
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> They think Michelle?
>> Yeah.
>> I am somewhat afraid that
Jon could be playing me.
>> Crack it open.
>> It's just that he is talking
with Shawn and Burton and
Michelle with such truth in his
eyes, and I see it and observe
it every day, and he does the
same thing to me, and it just
makes me feel uneasy.
I just wish that he would talk
to them a little bit less
convincingly.
>> Do you want a little sugar
in your drink?
>> Don't drop it, dude.
>> Hey, you need to not drop it.
(laughs)
Whew!
>> I am so stoked to go to
Tribal Council.
I am stoked!
I want to see it.
I can't wait.
I think it's going to be
awesome.
Ric Flair is voted off the
island.
Knowing that I'm going nowhere.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're
going to get funky like a
monkey.
The game's going great for
Jonny Fairplay.
I got a one-on-one alliance with
Shawn.
I got a five-way alliance with
myself, Trish, Rupert, Christa
and Sandra.
And I have a four-way alliance
with myself, Shawn, Burton and
Michelle.
He can do the strut, too!
He can do the strut twice as
fast!
I'm having a blast.
It's even more fun than I
imagined.
I'm on paradise, and, uh,
I'm a... I'm a freakin' puppet
master.
That's all a guy can ask for.
>> Turn around!
Turn around!
>> Look at his white heinie.
There's, like, this red back and
then there's this pure white
heinie.
>> That's a sight to be had
right there.
>> Darth Vader!
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
I want you to grab a torch,
approach the flame, dip it and
get fire.
We do this because fire
represents your life in this
game.
As long as you have fire,
you're in the game.
When your fire's gone, so are
you.
Once you have fire, put it in a
slot and take a seat.
For the first time, we have the
Drake Tribe at Tribal Council,
minus Rupert, temporarily a
member of the Morgan Tribe.
So, he can't be voted out
tonight.
Jon, give me the state of
affairs for this tribe.
>> Awesome, awesome, awesome,
awesome.
Happy tribe.
That's it.
Good tribe, couldn't be happier.
>> PROBST: Are you loaded?
>> Yeah.
(laughs)
Like, you know, this isn't the
happiest of occasions, but you
might as well make it as happy
as possible.
>> PROBST: Michelle, any
friendships developing 12 days
in?
>> Tons of friendships.
Everybody's a friend.
We've, uh, been through some
really strange, wild times
together, and everybody's kind
of keeping an open mind about
the situation.
And we do come together more
than... than I thought we did,
so it's hard not to become
friends with people.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
yesterday's challenge.
I'm still a little confused.
A very physical challenge, the
first challenge we've had like
that, and you sit out Rupert and
Burton, two of your strongest
guys.
And they tell me it's rotation
with immunity at stake.
Christa, is that true?
>> Yeah, I think it's only fair.
All of us want to have the
opportunity to participate.
I mean, we only get the chance
one in a lifetime to be out
here.
>> PROBST: Is there a
double-edged sword, Burton, to
being a very successful tribe?
The good news is you're not
losing anybody.
The bad news is you can't get
rid of anybody.
>> That's true.
It is great to win everything
because you avoid immunity,
but at the same time you have
absolutely no control over the
game itself.
At some point that can come back
to haunt you because if you
wanted to send someone home,
you wouldn't have the
opportunity to.
>> PROBST: Jon, self-proclaimed
"good strategist," what are you
basing your vote on tonight?
>> Um, by whatever the
astrological signs tell me.
>> PROBST: Is that a respectful
way to treat somebody that
you've lived with for 12 days?
>> Maybe, maybe not.
We'll find out in a few minutes.
>> PROBST: It is time to vote.
Trish, you're up.
>> (whispers): You're the
biggest threat that we have.
We'll see you, buddy.
>> Christa, this is a tough...
tough game, but I'm making
strategic decisions.
>> Now, can you dig that,
sucker?
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Christa.
Burton.
One vote Burton, one vote
Christa.
That's two votes Christa.
Burton.
Two votes Burton, two votes
Christa.
Burton.
That's three votes Burton,
two votes Christa.
First member of the Drake Tribe
voted out...
Burton.
That's four votes.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Last vote will remain a mystery.
Burton, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, there was a lot of talk
tonight about one big happy
tribe.
It should be interesting back at
camp.
Grab your torches.
You can head back.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
A voting betrayal is exposed.
>> I know what Shawn wrote on
his card.
>> My card said "Burton."
>> PROBST: With Rupert at
Morgan, Drake worries.
>> My concern with Rupert
is that he's giving away too
much information about us and
not realizing it.
>> PROBST: And things are
looking up for Morgan.
>> Probably the smartest thing
this tribe ever did was get a
hold of Rupert.
>> I'm, uh, disappointed beyond
what words could explain.
But, being a strategic player
and knowing the threat that I
posed in my tribe, I probably
would've done what the majority
ended up doing.
It's going to be a lot harder
without me.
Uh, challenges are not going to
be guaranteed as they were when
I was involved.
Good luck to those left, and
I'll see you on the other side.