>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor: Rupert had some
regrets after his first Tribal
Council.
I can't believe
I wrote Michelle's name down
instead of Shawn.
>> PROBST: And he Morgan Tribe
had a visit from a Panamanian
local.
( bird squawks )
>> I think it's hilarious
that Osten is scared of every
little thing.
>> PROBST: At Drake...
>> Dude, you do more not to do
work than doing work!
>> PROBST: ...Shawn had worn
out his welcome.
>> SANDRA: Shawn should get a
clue or he's going home.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge: First part of
today's reward: steak.
ALL: Oh...
>> PROBST: Drake took aim at
Morgan...
Drake wins reward!
( all cheering ) ...and savored
their victory.
>> This is the bomb.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, the tribes' minds
and bodies were pushed to the
limit, and Morgan was the
last tribe standing.
Morgan wins immunity.
Facing Tribal
Council, Shawn was on the
chopping block until Trish
and Jon felt threatened by
Rupert.
>> TRISH: One person has
a hell of a lot of power
right now.
>> JON: There's no way
anyone can go against Rupert
to the final two.
It'd be a freakin' K.O., man.
They're planning on getting
rid of you tonight.
>> PROBST: But Rupert turned the
tables with a plan of his own by
going to Shawn for support.
>> I'm with you on that, baby.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Trish and Jon's plan was
foiled when Shawn sided with
Rupert.
Sixth person voted out
of the Pearl Island: Trish.
The tribes are now even at
five members each.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> RUPERT: Who the hell voted
for me?
Who the hell voted for me?
Jon?
>> Yeah.
>> Who the hell voted for me?
>> I did.
>> What the ... was that ...
tonight?
>> I was down for Drake, dude,
I would have made a decision...
>> Damn it, look at me!
>> I'm looking at you.
>> What the ... was that ...
>> I made a decision
based on... You're starting
>> You're starting this ... now!
Damn it.
At Tribal Council,
I dodged the biggest
cannonball aimed right at me.
I knew when I saw two
"Ruperts" in the vote,
that Trish and Jon were
against me.
I was ready to
kill Jon, literally grab that
little scrawny ass by the neck
and pop his head off him like
a ... chicken.
I'm out there kicking my ass
to get you ... damn fish
and you ... turn the tribe
against me!
>> I didn't turn
the ... tribe against you.
>> Who did?
>> Hey, it wasn't my...
>> The... the person that's gone
right now is the person that
came up with the idea.
>> Who voted for me?
>> I did.
>> I ... realized it
today that she was lying to me
the whole time-- deceiving the
tribe, telling all kinds of
stories, different versions.
>> She had it in the bag.
She had you guys locked up,
she had Jon locked up.
>> CHRISTA: And Jon's trying to
pass it off right now, like,
"Oh, I wasn't part of the
whole plan." Listen.
>> JON: I want to know why
I wasn't included in the
conversation.
>> Included?
In ... me?
You ... me!
You were included.
>> I didn't...
Hey, I made the decision based
on Drake.
>> Drake made the decision.
You were the odd man out.
>> JON: I've never seen a
guy more mad in my entire
life.
I mean, he's right in
my face.
He's ready to punch me.
But if there were to be a
merge, Rupert's absolutely a
threat.
I mean, he could
switch on a dime.
He says he'd never do it,
but it pissed me off when
he... when he helped Morgan win
that challenge, and, uh, I...
I'm not the kind of guy that
forgives or forgets
You said in your own words,
"If any one of us went over to
Morgan, that they would vote
them off. "However, you did say
if there was one person that
could go over there, they
wouldn't do that to, it would
be you.
>> I never said that in
a ... million years.
>> Well, I was under the
impression that you did.
>> Who the hell would even have
the ... arrogance
to say that?
>> I... I thought that was a
ballsy ass statement.
>> Why... if
I thought that, why wouldn't I
have stayed there and made the
Morgans stronger?
>> Well, I... I don't know.
Well, I have no clue.
That, that makes... that makes
a lot of sense.
>> I would have
stayed there and said, "You
Drakes are dead."
>> And I was
scared to death that you were
going to turn on us.
>> I am the
one person that will always
stand true to Drake.
>> I was following some...
>> You were following Trish, who
was telling every one of us
you and me are going to be the
final two.
She was telling
every one of us that.
Let's start fresh.
>> All right.
It sucks, man. I'm sorry.
>> We're all done,
and we'll be five strong
Drakes, okay?
>> All right.
>> We're to be five strong
Drake.
>> Yep.
>> RUPERT: I'm not saying Jon is
finished yet, but...
( sighs )
I'm not saying that I believe
him at all anymore.
I don't
believe a damn word he says.
>> I'm sorry, man.
I don't know why I believed
that, I just did.
>> Jonny Fairplay
is Jonny Pain-In-The-Ass now
to me.
(thunder)
(wind whistling)
>> Bull ... rain, go away.
I can't even get out in the
ocean; I get pounded around,
try to get a fish.
>> ANDREW: Day 19.
A little worn out.
I think there's a direct
correlation between lack of
protein in our bodies and
energy, and then Rupert came
over for a couple of days.
We had some fish, dramatic
increase in energy-- I felt
like a new person.
Right now,
we'd probably give anything
to have Rupert over here.
In fact, we definitely would
give anything to have Rupert
over here.
>> Dude, there's a stingray
right there. Dude, dude, dude!
Whoa, he's right there.
You see him?
He's right there.
Yes!
>> He's long gone now, pal.
>> It's not that we don't want
the fish, it's that we're
having great difficulty
catching them.
This is the most
I've ever eat beans in my
whole life.
>> You can only eat
so many beans.
>> RYNO: Why's that?
>> 'Cause they suck.
( Tijuana laughs )
>> TIJUANA: We
only have two portions of rice
left.
>> OSTEN: It's imperative
that we merge.
It's imperative.
'Cause, I'm...
I'm bigger than everybody else.
I'm, like, 200 pounds.
I'm probably like 175 right now.
I have no energy to do
anything, and, uh...
it's wearing on me.
>> ANDREW: It's so difficult
because we know if we had as
much fish as the Drake Tribe
has, we'd be having parties
every night, dancing and
singing.
I can't imagine
having my own fish.
It just...
it's depressing to think
about, actually; I'd rather
not think about it.
>> RYNO: Think if, uh, Skinny
Ryan were still... still here.
>> He would have perished.
>> ( laughing ): He would
perish.
>> Yeah.
>> So would Lill.
>> TIJUANA: Yeah, I think so,
too.
>> ANDREW: You know, it gets
mentally overwhelming
and draining to think about
all the things we need to do
just to survive out here, and
it's exhausting.
>> I'm tired today.
>> My entire body aches.
>> And you can see on my tribe
mates, it's taking their toll.
O. T., this morning,
he has good days and he has
bad days; this morning he
checked out-- I could see it
in his eyes, I could read it
a mile away.
He's... he's somewhere.
He's not here.
He didn't sleep at all last
night from what I could see
'cause he kept me up, but
he'll rally if we need him
for something... hopefully.
>> SHAWN: I'm curious to see
what's going on today.
I've got a hunch, baby.
I got more than a hunch.
I know this is the biggest sea
mail we'll ever see.
>> RUPERT: My tribe, they have
it in their heads that we're
going to a new island
and having a big party
and going to go with Morgans
and be in a merge.
>> All right, guys, here we go.
>> If it happens, okay, but I'm
not looking forward to it,
because I have a strong
tribe right now, I do not
want to merge yet, and I
cannot plan on a merge yet.
>> All right, here we go. You
ready? This could decide the
future. Whoa, wait a second
here. We got a lock and keys.
>> SANDRA: One more challenge.
I'd take a challenge in a
minute.
>> "The most important
reward for which your tribe
"will compete needs you to
work together "and be quick on
your feet. "It's better than
steak and lobster, "will be
the sweetest victory you'll
know, but if the other tribe
gets it, it would seem a
painful blow."
>> I think we're
going to be locked together
and we have to get certain
keys to unlock us.
"It will be
the sweetest victory you'll
know."
>> Well, we shall soon find
out, huh?
>> Make some popcorn
before we go?
>> I would love to
try some of that.
>> SANDRA: On
our way back from, uh, the
tree mail, Jon mentioned,
"Hey, you know what? We
should open up a coconut."
And, uh, Rupert, Christa,
myself and Jon had said,
"Okay, we want the coconut
popcorn." Because once you fry
the coconut, it tastes exactly
like popcorn.
>> SHAWN: I don't
even... you know what, to be
honest, we're not cooking it.
'Cause, we don't really have
time.
Yeah, we'll cook the
next one.
>> We don't have the
other one. Let's just do it.
That's not...
>> I'll share this
one with them, and then you
can cook that one, Jon.
>> They would want it cooked.
Jon, stop arguing. They've
already said. Everyone said.
>> You argue about everything.
>> Does Rupert want it cooked?
>> Do we have time to sit
here and worry about this ...
right now?
>> We wor... We're doing it.
You're the only one
working against that.
>> Do it.
>> Well, you can help, and that
would speed up the process.
>> I don't want to help...
>> I know you don't, because
that's not your decision.
>> Are you going to make this
a ...
difficult thing every ... day,
already? Come on, now.
>> JON: Yes! Obviously!
>> It's always an argument with
you.
>> Four out of five people
said...
>> You're about to cry again
over a... over a...
>> You're an ass ..., dude.
>> Excuse me?
>> You're an ass ...
>> You want to sit here and call
me an ass ...
We're gonna go
take care of this, 'cause you
are not sitting and calling me
an ass ... anymore, all right?
You're a ... all right?
Enough, all right?
>> Dude, get out of my face.
>> No. Don't even
tell me to get out of your
face.
>> SANDRA: Cut it out.
>> SHAWN: You know what your
problem is, Jon?
You're a little baby.
>> JON: I'm not hiding....
>> Be a man.
>> A man doesn't fight
someone, you ... !
A ... Neanderthal does.
There's a ... difference.
>> We have about 20 minutes.
>> Exactly, we have enough time
to ... make popcorn, you ...
>> Call me a ...
again, Jon, I swear to God...
>> You threaten me with physical
violence one more ... time,
man... Threat... I want you to,
dude! 'Cause I want to see
you ... walk away!
>> Don't cry like a ... baby if
you're...
>> SANDRA: They're
always fighting. I'm glad
it's not me. Let them duke
it out. You know, let them
kill each other, vote each
other off. As long as it ain't
Sandra, I'm happy.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
19 days you've been out here
in the Pearl Islands.
You have
survived the bugs, the lack of
food, miserable living
conditions, and the
ever-shifting tribal dynamics.
Together, you voted six people
out of this game, three from
Morgan, three from Drake.
The reasons you voted these
people out varied.
The only
real common trait among the
six people you voted out is
that they're no longer in this
game-- but that may soon
change.
Morgan, Drake, your
past has come back to haunt
you.
Come on in, guys.
>> OSTEN: No way.
>> SANDRA: What's that?
>> PROBST: The six people you
have voted outs
return now as a third tribe.
Nicole, Skinny Ryan, Lill,
Burton, Michelle and Trish.
Do you guys have a tribe name?
>> We're the Outcasts.
>> PROBST: The Outcasts.
Not unlike the
pirate days, they got tired of
somebody, felt they were no
longer worthy, they shipped
them out to sea and left them
for dead.
Typically, they died,
but every so often, they
didn't, and when they came
back, they usually had one
thing on their mind.
I'm guessing it's the same with
you. Michelle?
>> Revenge, baby.
All about revenge.
>> PROBST: All right, guys.
Let's get to it.
Here's how it will work-- the
Outcasts will compete against
Morgan and Drake in a
three-tribe challenge, and the
stakes are severe.
If Morgan
or Drake lose to the Outcast
tribe, you will go to Tribal
Council tonight and you will
vote somebody out.
The Outcasts will then go to
Tribal Council and vote
somebody in and replace the
member you lost.
If both tribes
lose to the Outcasts, you both
will go to Tribal-- separately.
Both will vote somebody out,
and two Outcasts will come
back into this game.
In addition, if any Outcast
makes it back into this game,
they are immune at the next
Tribal Council to give them
a fair shot at integrating
with their new tribe and
getting back into this game.
If the Outcasts kick your ass,
you may be going home.
On the flip side, if you really
are the ten most worthy
survivors,
this should be no trouble.
Drake, Morgan, just so you
know, the Outcasts have been
living on very limited rations
of rice and fruit and protein,
just like you.
Okay. Want to
know what the challenge is?
ALL: Yeah.
>> PROBST: It's a first.
It is a three-tribe challenge.
It's a series of rescues.
There are three prisons with
three cages in each one.
Your entire tribe will be
locked up, except for one
tribe rescuer.
On my "go,"
rescuers will race to the beach
to retrieve their flag. Each
flag is an equal distance
from the tribe prison.
Using your hands, start digging
under and into the first cage
where you will release your
first tribe mate, who's tied
up. Together, you will dig
into the second cage and
release two more tribe mates
who are also tied up.
On the ground, you'll find
scattered sticks and string.
Use those to build a pole
and reach for two keys in
the third cage, which will
unlock that door. Those keys
will also unlock the rest of
your tribe. Now, everybody's
in the last cage and you
need to get out of that
final door. Use your pole
again to retrieve one last
key from outside the prison.
First tribe, with their flag,
to cross the finish line wins.
For the Outcasts, you're
fighting to get back in this
game.
Drake and Morgan, you're
fighting to stay alive.
All right. Select your tribe
rescuers. Wait for my "go."
All right, the rescuers you
chose for your tribes: Burton
for the Outcasts, Andrew for
Morgan, Shawn for Drake.
A lot at stake.
Survivors ready?
Go!
( cheering )
Burton out to an early lead.
Savage behind.
Shawn bringing up the rear.
Burton has his flag and he's
heading back. Shawn has his
flag. Savage has his flag.
( teams shouting
encouragement )
Burton is
first back, puts his flag in
and starts digging.
Shawn digging,
Savage right there.
>> Dig, Burton!
Go! Dig!
You're almost there!
>> PROBST: Burton trying to get
under.
>> Shove yourself!
>> PROBST: Burton,
for the Outcasts,
first through the cage.
Starting to untie Trish.
Shawn is through for Drake.
>> Come on.
Forget the flag!
>> Here, get the other one.
>> PROBST: Keep it going,
Savage. He's got it.
Going to get through.
Good job!
Savage through for Morgan.
>> Bunch of double knots...
>> PROBST: Got to start untying
Ryno.
>> Right here.
>> PROBST: All three rescuers
are in the first cage.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Shawn and Christa
for Drake start digging into
their second cage.
Burton and Trish
for the Outcasts right on
their tail.
>> Come on, guys!
>> PROBST: All three tribes,
guys, are in the first cage.
It's anybody's game.
Ryno untied for Morgan.
Christa through to
the second cage for Drake.
Trish through to the second cage
for the Outcasts.
>> Get her! Get her! Get her!
>> That's okay. Come here. Come
here, Chris. Come here!
>> PROBST: Shawn through.
Both Drake members now on the
second cage.
Drake with a
slight lead over the Outcasts.
Morgan still struggling.
Burton's under.
Now, both Outcasts are through
to the second cage.
Andrew Savage squeezing under.
Morgan, you're still in last
place. Pick it up, guys.
Burton starting to work on
Michelle.
Rupert'suntied.
He goes to work on a pole.
A lot of challenge left.
Keep fighting.
Ryno's through.
All three tribes now in the
second cage.
Drake and the
Outcasts have everybody free.
Morgan still trying to untie
tribe members.
>> Give me another one.
Give me another one.
>> PROBST: T's almost free.
It's now a race.
You got to build a pole
to get those keys that'll get
you in the third cage.
Drake working together.
Outcasts taking their time,
building a long, strong pole.
Osten's free.
Everybody now free for Morgan.
All three tribes are now working
on their pole.
You got to get those first keys.
>> Go.
>> We're fine here.
We're fine here. here.
>> Good.
>> We're fine here.
>> Hold on. Hold on.
>> Hold on.
>> PROBST: Rupert has the first
set of keys for Drake.
Burton going for the first set
of keys for the Outcasts.
Drake, first tribe into that
last cage.
>> Hold on.
>> There you go. Easy, easy,
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
>> All right.
>> Grab it. Grab it.
>> PROBST: The Outcasts now have
their keys, about to get into
that last cage.
Drake working it,
going for that final key.
This'll get them out
all together.
Morgan with the pole,
but they're still back
working on their first keys.
The Outcasts are into the
final cage.
It's Outcasts and Drake
neck and neck.
Osten... working it.
Morgan still struggling.
Pole about to break.
>> Double. Double lock.
>> PROBST: Drake's pole's
falling apart.
>> Go! Go! Go!
>> PROBST: Outcasts going for
that final key,
if the pole holds strong.
Morgan into the last cage.
It's now a race-- who can get
that key first?!
Outcasts very close
to a major upset.
Somebody could be coming back
into this game.
Don't want to drop those keys.
That pole is starting to bend.
>> Easy!
>> Shh! Shh! Shh!
>> Here we are. We got it.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: The Outcasts dropped
their keys.
>> Come on. Hold on.
>> No, no, no, Lill, you gotta
stay in.
>> Hold on.
>> It's okay.
>> PROBST: Morgan and Drake
fighting to stay alive.
>> Come on.
>> Be careful. Be careful!
Be careful!
>> PROBST: Morgan's pole has
just fallen apart.
Outcasts have their keys,
unlocking the last lock.
This could be it.
Drake trying to catch up.
The Outcasts working together
as a tribe, untying the door.
>> BURTON: Go!
>> Get it! Come on!
>> PROBST: Everybody's got to
cross the finish line,
got to have the tribe flag.
( yelling and cheering )
Michelle's through,
Burton's through.
Ryan is through!
The Outcasts defeat Morgan and
Drake!
This challenge is over.
It's over.
(cheering, accolades continue)
Huge effort by all three tribes.
I know there's a lot going on
emotionally, but for the
Outcasts, clearly a big win,
terrific opportunity.
But let's face it,
you guys have had your own
ups and downs in this game.
Burton, how big a victory is
this?
>> Revenge is sweet, but...
it's been no walk in the park,
and you want to talk about
being down, man, got kicked
out of a tribe.
Those are the lowest of the
lows.
They haven't been there yet.
So, uh, we faced a lot of
adversity and came back
stronger than ever.
>> PROBST: Okay, here's how
it's gonna work:
Drake... you will come to
Tribal Council first tonight,
you'll vote somebody out.
They will be going home.
Morgan...
you will follow them in a
separate Tribal Council.
You will vote somebody out.
They'll be going home.
The Outcasts... you'll come in
last, you'll vote two people
into the game, and they'll
report to their new tribes
immediately.
Make sense?
Head back the way you came.
See you at Tribal Council.
>> ANDREW: The game to end all
games.
It's frustrating,
it's exhilarating, it's
exciting, and it's a pain in
the ass.
Those six in the...
the misfits... have no right
to be here.
>> None. None.
All right? So I want
everyone's word, looking me in
the eye.
Whoever they send
over here is gone the very next
opportunity.
We got that?
>> RYNO: They got immunity on
the first one. The first one.
>> You're kidding.
>> It doesn't matter though.
It'll be three on two.
Bye-bye.
>> ANDREW: Well, we need to
strategize.
I don't want any
of those misfits getting any
control or authority in our
tribe.
>> No. No way. I don't...
>> I don't care about Drake.
Anybody that left Morgan,
there's a damn good
reason for it.
Skinny Ryan has no business
stepping on this beach again.
Lill-- God bless her-- I love
her... she's got no business
competing in those challenges.
>> TIJUANA: For the most part,
we're all frustrated about
the new dynamic to this game.
And it was very obvious
that Andrew did not want
this new tribe member to
really have a say.
I think that
Andrew's very comfortable
being the leader.
He's got the
best seat in the house, um...
and I think he wants to keep
that.
>> Worst-case scenario,
we'll vote somebody out
tomorrow, and it can't be the
( bleep ) who joined us.
( groans )
>> I'd be the first one voted
off.
Vote me right off, 'cause I
don't deserve to win. Okay?
You guys stuck it out.
Your body could last longer than
mine. Mine couldn't.
I'm out of gas. I'm spent.
I couldn't even move in that
challenge today.
My temple has
got nothing to offer for me.
I'm... I'm a bag of atrophy
right now.
Anybody knows me
knows, when I come to play
at anything, it's 110%.
And, if I can't give that, I'm
out.
I like to win straight
up, and I can't do that.
Number two, I don't really
give a damn what someone else
thinks about me.
If you don't
like what I do or what I say or
what I've done, you can get in
line to kiss my ass.
For me to stay any longer
just makes me look like a fool.
And you can cut your losses.
You know, you're not going to
win everything.
>> You're sure?
I'm positive. Vote me off.
It's been a pleasure.
It's been a pleasure with all
you guys.
I just don't have it
in the tank anymore.
I don't have it in the tank
anymore.
>> TIJUANA: I'm not going to say
anything to Osten to make him
stay.
He had already
initially thought about
quitting quite a while ago.
I had something to say then
because I thought he had
more in him.
This time around, I don't... I
don't have anything to say to
Osten.
>> I can't sleep.
Every bone in my body is so
sore.
It's... it's unbearable, so...
You guys been good.
>> ANDREW: I think that O.T.
mentally and physically has
shut down.
He wants out, but
I feel, given any state of
facts, the last thing in the
world I would do is quit.
>> That's something he'll have
to live with for the rest of his
life.
>> And I don't think that
he's going to fully appreciate
it until it... it's obviously
too late.
>> SANDRA: That was terrible.
Horrible, horrible, horrible.
Who would have thought
they'd come back to haunt us?
When I first saw the
Outcast tribe, I was, like,
no way!
And then to see
Burton as their leader-- he's
so strong-- and everyone, I
know, was probably full of
anger and energy.
Who, do you think, is going to
come back?
>> Burton and Lill.
If those are the two...
You can't assume that, though.
Burton is not going to go down
without a fight.
>> I think it'll
be Michelle and Lill.
>> You wonder why those guys
were so happy about winning,
it's because they're a bunch
of losers that got a second
chance in life.
If you're a winner, you don't
have to go through the second
chance, uh, game.
So, you know, they're used to
that-- their entire lives,
they've been losers.
This is no different.
Well, somebody
has to go home.
Who wants to volunteer?
Raise your hand right now.
>> Anybody?
Hey, don't everybody jump up
at the same time.
Did anybody raise their hand?
>> No.
>> RUPERT: I don't feel
vulnerable tonight.
I have my three.
I'm not vulnerable tonight.
The two other guys
in the tribe are vulnerable.
Jon wrote my name down last
night, and fair is fair.
I should write Jon's name down
tonight, but I haven't
decided yet.
>> I mean, both of
them I would love to see...
>> RUPERT: Gone. Both of them
are lying their asses off to
us.
>> SANDRA: What if you asked
them to give their reasons why
they feel right now that they
should stay, and see what they
say?
>> They'd both say, "Because
he's a bigger liar.
Because he's telling you this,
he's telling you that."
>> But ask them.
Say, "We can't decide
on which one of you two will
go home, and we want to hear
why you should stay."
And let them fight it amongst
themselves.
>> That would be hilarious.
>> You want to?
You want to?
RUPERT: Hey, Jon.
I have been talking with the
ladies, and I can't decide who
I'm voting for.
I want both of you, if you
would, this is your chance to
sit down and just say why we
should keep you.
>> SANDRA: No fighting.
Two minutes, 'cause we're
leaving in five.
>> The way feel it is, you know,
I feel I've been pretty honest
as much as I could be up to
this point, but, um, Jon, you
know, I feel like I can't trust
him.
With the vote for you
yesterday, with the fact that
if we were to go into a merge
today and Jon didn't feel that
we were all with him, you
know, that that could be
dangerous for us.
>> Jon thought
he had it all in the bag.
He thought he was playing us
all and he had this whole game
figured out.
>> SHAWN: But I'm
going to do everything in my
power to make sure it's game
over for him.
You know, you
can't mess with me long
before I come back and get you.
>> I feel that, uh, I've...
I've shown that I'm loyal to
Drake.
Um, and I also feel that
I'm definitely a much harder
worker, so... and I think
that's important when it comes
to, uh, to everyday living.
>> JON: I know it's between
myself and Shawn.
I'm sure Rupert's not happy
that I wrote his name on a
piece of paper last night.
But, uh, will he forgive and
forget?
I don't know. We'll see.
>> PROBST: Well, I think the
walk in says it all.
I've never seen
you guys this quiet,
this separated.
I know you didn't expect to be
here again this soon.
Rupert, you're already shaking
your head.
>> Two days in a row.
Two days in a row.
Never would I
have thought we'd be here two
days in a row.
>> PROBST: Christa, what
was your reaction at the
challenge?
>> Oh, it was a little shocking.
I... I wasn't quite
expecting, uh, everybody else
to show back up.
I'm happy
that I really haven't
bad-mouthed anybody from our
own tribe that's over there.
>> PROBST: One of the unique
things about
today's change of events
is, you got to hear from people
who've been voted out.
Burton made a pretty honest
comment about, "You think you're
down?
You don't know down
until you've been voted out."
Sandra, did that hit you at
all as a, "Wow, I never thought
about how these guys have been
feeling"?
>> Definitely.
And with those words, you also
say, "Damn, they're going to
give it their all and they're
going to come back."
And now I do feel a little bit
threatened because the way he
sounded, he's ready to come
back today, so I wouldn't be
surprised if he walked back
into camp.
>> PROBST: Burton?
>> Burton.
Burton.
>> PROBST: The guy you couldn't
wait get rid of may be coming
home to roost again.
>> That's right.
>> PROBST: So, what happened
when you went back to camp?
>> Um, when we
got back to camp, um,
just before we came out here,
Rupert told the guys, "Okay,
you got two minutes apiece.
Tell us why we should keep you
around." And they said what
they had to say and, um, I
think we won't make our minds
up until we get up there and,
uh, cast our vote, so...
>> PROBST: So, Sandra, is it
safe for me, based
on what I'm hearing, to draw
the conclusion that it is
Shawn or Jon tonight that is
going home?
>> It is Shawn or Jon
that's going home tonight.
>> PROBST: Shawn, why not vote
you out tonight?
What are you going to
bring to this tribe that's
crumbling by the moment?
>> I'm dedicated to this tribe,
and I wish we could just wash
the slate from the past and go
forward as strong as we can,
because the only way that this
tribe is going to be powerful
is if we all stick together
and trust each other no matter
what, and I feel that I can be
a good part of that.
>> PROBST: Jon, convince
these guys.
Why not vote you out tonight?
>> I feel I care more about
this tribe than I do myself.
Uh, I feel that I know how to
split a coconut five ways as
opposed to Shawn.
I think I have shown
tribe loyalty, which, uh, I
don't know what, uh, Shawn to
be loyal to at all.
So, that's pretty much it.
>> PROBST: With that, it is time
to vote.
Rupert, you're up.
>> Jon...
you and I know the truth.
Basically, you've been
backstabbing everyone
including myself.
>> (bleep) you.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave the
Tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote... Shawn.
Jon.
That's one vote Jon,
one vote Shawn.
Shawn.
That's two votes Shawn, one
vote Jon.
The latest member to
be voted out of the Drake
tribe-- Shawn.
That's three votes, that's
enough. You need to bring me
your torch.
Shawn, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Maybe tonight you
reached your lowest point.
If it's any consolation,
Morgan is up next
to vote off one of their own.
And soon, you will both have
new tribe members.
What you do
from this point forward
will define your destiny in
this game.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
I should have seen this one
coming.
Jon basically went
back on everything he had
told me for the first three
days, um, about our supposed
alliance.
I had hoped that
today would have brought a
merger.
Um, things probably
would have been a lot
different and I might have
been able to go a lot
further. I don't know.
What can I say? Game, set,
match.
( thunder crashing )
>> PROBST: Well, Drake has been
here and gone.
They were lucky
with the weather.
Unfortunately, you're not.
Been a while since you guys
have been here.
Had a nice run.
Savage,
what happened when you guys
got back to camp?
Suddenly you're faced with
an unexpected Tribal Council
and you're going to have to
vote somebody out.
>> As soon as
we get back to camp, Osten
steps forward, says that his
mind and his body have shut
down and that he needs to go.
He can't take it another day,
absolutely insists that we put
his name on the parchment and
vote him out tonight.
>> PROBST: You had
enough, Osten?
>> Uh, going into
this, I was like, "I'll only
go as far as my body will
allow me to go." And right
now, my body's done.
Exasperated.
Every bone in my body hurts.
I just can't go any further.
I'll be more of a liability
than an asset to my team,and
I refuse to do that.
>> PROBST: Savage,
how much of this experience
is about finding out
what you are made of?
>> It's all about that, Jeff.
It's all mental.
Your mind controls your body.
If your body's shutting down,
it's because, in my opinion,
it's because your mind's
shutting down.
>> PROBST: Okay, so, Osten,
your body, although it appears
to smack anybody's body that's
still left in this game, I
would argue probably your mind
has had enough, as well.
So, when you hear a guy
like Burton come back and say
today, "You don't know what
down is until you've been
humiliated by being voted out,"
and yet he still has a burning
desire enough to be back in
this game that he'll risk it
again, is there any part of
you that questions your own
will to go on when your body
may be saying, "I'm tired"?
>> Absolutely not. I equate my
temple to a car.
If it has no gas, it cannot run.
>> PROBST: T,
from what I gathered at that
second Tribal Council, it was
Osten who was the mysterious
person who wanted to quit.
So, this goes back to day five
or six.
What's going on from
your point of view right now
with Osten?
>> Um, I can't dictate
to Osten or understand where
he's coming from.
This experience may not be
enough of a sacrifice for him
versus his health.
It is for me.
I'm willing to go until
probably I'm dead here, either
that or I'm voted out, but
that's just me.
>> PROBST: Darrah, I'm
watching your body shrink by
the day, pulling your top up,
nothing's staying on
Do you want out of this game?
>> No, I do not want out of this
game.
Like T said, you know,
I guess you'll have to be
carrying me away because I'm
not going to leave this game
until I have to.
>> PROBST: Ryno, what's
your take on this happening
tonight?
Is it, "You know what?
Fine, Osten. You've wanted to
quit twice. Go home"?
>> As far as I'm concerned, if
it was me, I'd be clawing and
scratching and have to have
pneumonia and stuff, but you
know, Osten's going to do his
thing.
That's... that's his
wishes.
I'm going to grant him
his wishes.
>> PROBST: So, I'm going to
go back to you, Osten.
I think you know I'm not
picking on you.
>> Oh, that's
fine if you are.
>> PROBST: So, when you
hear your four other tribe
mates, who obviously adore you,
when you hear them say,
"I wouldn't quit, not for
nothing, Jeff," you can't tell
me somewhere in the back of
your mind, there's not a little
part of you saying, "I am
quitting."
>> It's... take it for
whatever you want
I mean, if you want to say
quitting,
you want to say stopping,
yeah, I'm quitting.
My health
to me is more important to me,
um, than the million dollars,
I guess, right now.
Does the
mean justify the ends?
No, it doesn't.
>> PROBST: Let me ask you
something, Osten.
Have you wondered what
the hell you're doing out here?
>> You know what? I'm clearly
out of my element.
As a situation,
I would have thought that,
"Hey, give it a shot."
I can at least say, "Hey, I went
and tried it."
I like to have been
successful.
Apparently, I'm not
going to be, but, you know, I
won't live my life saying,
"What if."
>> PROBST: Savage, you're
shaking your head.
>> If I were to do this,
I would have a
"What if," flat out.
What if I went another two days?
What if I went one more day?
I mean, but that's just me.
You know, I... I don't pretend
to-to walk in his shoes, Jeff.
I-I can't understand what
he's going through.
It's his decision.
>> PROBST: Well, Osten,
I don't pretend to know what
you're thinking either, but I
know this-- I've been at about
a hundred Tribal Councils, never
ever seen anybody lay down
their torch.
So this is a first for me.
Seems unanimous.
I just want to make sure.
Savage, you're going to indulge
Osten, send him home?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Darrah?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Ryno?
>> PROBST: T?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: No need to vote and
waste any more time.
Grab your torch.
>> PROBST: Osten, per your
wishes...
go home.
With all due respect to Osten,
people work too damn hard to
get in this game and fight to
stay alive.
If he wants to lay
his torch down, so it shall be.
Who knows?
Maybe this is the best thing
to happen to the Morgan Tribe.
All I know is, you will head
back to camp.
Soon after,
a new tribe member will arrive,
and I can promise you this--
that person wants to be in
this game.
Grab your torches,
head on back. Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor-- Drake and Morgan
dread the arrival of their
new tribe members.
>> Who is gonna come to our
tribe?
>> If it's Burton, I will fall
out.
>> And I'll be damned if
one of those Outcasts is
ever going to get a foothold
in the Morgan Tribe.
>> PROBST: And at Tribal Council
Council...
Time to find out who's going
back into this game.