>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
At a combination
reward/immunity challenge, the
stakes were raised.
The winning tribe will select
one member from the losing
tribe to join them on the
reward, which means they avoid
Tribal Council.
(cheering)
Once the challenge got
underway, the competition
between Ethan and Boston Rob
was red-hot, but Chapera
pulled out a narrow victory.
Chapera wins reward and
immunity.
Chapera chose to kidnap Kathy,
saving her from Tribal Council.
Chapera, by the way, that's
your ride.
A 94-foot luxury yacht.
While enjoying a day of food
and fun, Kathy hit it off with
the rival tribe.
>> ♪ We got a new girl
Her name is Kat ♪
>> ♪ She fits in
just like that. ♪
>> PROBST: At Mogo Mogo, Colby
and Ethan agreed to get rid of
Jerri.
>> I think our decision
was made when Jerri Manthey
came on board.
I mean, that's the one we want
to get rid of.
>> PROBST: But Lex made a bold
play.
>> Their plan is to get
rid of you tonight.
That's not going to happen.
We're going to do Colby tonight.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Lex's gamble paid off, and
Colby was stunned when he
became the seventh person to
leave Survivor: All-Stars.
11 all-stars are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
(thunder rumbling)
(thunder crashing)
>> Is anybody here?
Hello?
Oh, they're still at the Tribal
Council.
Just how depressing is this?
(groans)
It's terrible coming back here.
Horrible.
It's empty.
They're going to come back
from Tribal Council.
They're going to want to know
what's going on.
I got automatic immunity.
They voted somebody off.
I had a ball.
(thunder cracks)
(grunts)
Ah, this is Suvivor at the
lowest.
I was sipping champagne on the
bow of a multimillion-dollar
yacht, and now I am soaking
wet trying to save this fire.
Oh, my God.
(thunder cracks)
(rain stops)
(indistinct talking)
>> You have a good time, Kathy?
>> I couldn't believe I
was standing here putting a
fire together and it started
to pour.
>> There, you got it.
>> The tribe got back
and they, you know, didn't
give me any hugs or anything,
which is interesting.
I got hugged by Chapera in a
second, but that's just not
this tribe.
>> The Tribal Council
was brutal tonight.
>> I bet it was.
Heard that Colby got voted out.
It was very somber and sad.
>> His hat, his pants,
his canteen.
>> His hat's not here, is it?
>> His hat's here.
>> I really want to send
that to him.
I hope we can.
>> We will.
>> Having Colby gone to me
is just, sort of summarizes
this tribe.
I don't think this tribe
amounted to a whole lot.
We were just kind of in the
middle, and I think Colby was
actually holding us back
because he didn't trust
anybody.
And it's too late.
I think it's too late for this
tribe to rally.
I will try to think more
positive thoughts, but it's
difficult because now Ethan is
questioning it all.
(thunder booms)
>> Colby didn't look
at anyone when he left.
>> I'm so surprised.
>> He didn't even look
behind him.
>> Yeah, just a turn around
around and a, you know...
>> I would have been like,
to Jerri after saying all those
things, I would have been, like,
"You got me."
>> That's too bad.
>> Ooh, don't I feel silly.
Wow.
The one vote was supposed to
be for me and the rest were
supposed to be for Jerri.
I thought everything was going
smoothly, and boom, you know?
Not only was Colby fooled and
voted out, but I was fooled
and had no idea.
(thunder rumbling)
I thought I was pretty close
to Lex.
Not anymore.
Not after Tribal Council.
Not after I was left out of
those plans.
When you feel a bond with
someone and they tell you
something, and then they rip
that bond apart by doing
something totally different,
that hurts.
(chuckling)
(laughing)
>> Yes, I feel like I'm
being evil right now, but, boy,
does it feel good.
>> Colby's gone.
I mean, what more can I say?
I've now officially lived out
one of my goals in this game,
and that is to make it longer
than Colby.
Knock, knock.
You hear that sound, Colby?
That's the bellboy, and he
just took all my baggage away.
So...
My closet is now clean.
My Survivor closet is clean.
>> We have tree mail.
>> All right.
Ooh... pretty bottle.
>> Very pretty.
>> Oh, my Gosh.
>> Oh, that's dinner.
>> "Pick one representative to
get on a boat and visit the
Mogo Mogo tribe camp.
Bring this message in a bottle
with you, open the bottle and
read the note aloud to the
Mogo Mogo tribe.
Follow the instructions.
Bring the pen."
>> Every single one of
us was scared to death.
Not one of us wanted to go.
We were so afraid that that
person might have to stay over
there.
So we decided to pull straws,
and Jenna ended up picking the
smallest straw.
It's Jenna.
>> You okay?
>> Yeah.
>> You sure you're all right?
So I just happened to get the
shortest straw.
I don't think it's a good thing.
>> All right, sweetheart.
Have fun.
>> Yes.
>> Have a good time, Jenna.
>> See if Ethan and my
alliance are still tight.
(laughing)
>> There's got be something
that when you go over there,
you're on the fence.
>> I think we should take
two things into consideration.
Nobody who doesn't want to go
should go, and the decision
should be one that everyone
finds agreeable.
>> I think Kathy might be a good
representative.
>> It's up to you guys
what you want to do.
I don't mind going over, but
we definitely had a good
rapport yesterday.
I know the players over there.
I know they accept me.
I know that the hair on the
back of neck won't stand up on
end if I get off the boat over
on their beach.
>> Bye, Kath.
We love you!
Look at that rainbow she's
sailing off into.
It's a good omen.
(indistinct talking)
>> Hey, welcome to Mogo Mogo.
>> How are you?
>> I'm great.
>> My guess is you have
a bottle.
>> I have a bottle and a pen.
(glass shatters)
"Dear representative, pick
three separate items from the
Mogo Mogo tribe that you feel
your tribe would like to play
for in today's reward challenge.
You cannot choose anyone's
personal items or clothing.
Write these items down on the
parchment provided in private.
Do not let anyone know your
choices.
Get back on your boat and
bring the parchment directly
to the challenge."
>> So that's how it's
going to be.
>> That's how it's going to be.
>> Thanks, guys. Hi.
I know, it's been so long.
>> Kathy was chosen to
come visit our tribe.
What she had to do was make a
list of three things to take
from our tribe.
>> "You cannot choose
anyone's personal items."
>> If you want to write Tom
down, he said...
>> Aww, he'll go.
>> Kathy acted like,
"I'm just going to take things
you guys don't need.
You're not even going to miss
them," you know?
And we're thinking, "Yeah,
right."
>> What's this, alcohol?
(groaning)
>> And of course we're
thinking, "Oh, man, our camp
is amazing, especially our
shelter."
We have a tarp, we have a
parachute, plus we have
blankets, we have pillows.
>> You guys, all this
stuff's going to fine, just so
you know.
>> We love you.
>> Whenever I have the
opportunity, I'm going to put
myself forward, 'cause
inevitably, you know, what
really works is networking
with the people.
>> You're the only one we
wanted to see.
>> I know, it's good to
see you guys, too.
>> PROBST: Representatives, come
on in.
How's it going, Kathy?
>> It's going well.
How 'bout you, Jeff?
>> PROBST: Good. Hey, Jenna.
>> Hello.
>> PROBST: Bring in the rest of
your tribe.
Chapera, come on in.
Mogo Mogo, come on in.
Okay, earlier today you each
selected a representative:
Kathy and Jenna.
Their job was to go to the other
camp and select three items that
they wanted to serve as rewards
should their tribe win.
They've written down the items
they selected.
It's a secret.
We'll reveal it in a minute.
I'll take those from you.
First, I'm going to explain the
challenge.
It is a log roll.
One at a time tribe members from
each tribe will square off-- man
versus man, woman versus woman.
First person to hit the water is
out.
The winner scores a point for
their tribe.
The first tribe to five wins the
reward.
See what you're playing for.
If Chapera wins, you will take
the following items from Mogo
Mogo's camp: grill, one bag of
rice and the Hawaiian sling.
If Mogo Mogo wins, they will
take the following items from
Chapera: one blanket, the
parachute siding and your tarp.
Because this is man versus man,
woman versus woman, Chapera, you
have one extra man so you will
sit out one man in this
challenge.
Who's out?
>> Big Tom.
>> PROBST: Big Tom's going to
sit out.
We will randomly draw numbers.
Wait for my go.
Here we go, first matchup:
Shii Ann and Alicia.
One foot on the black.
Start spinning.
>> You're going to have to spin
somewhere.
>> You're going to have
to spin somewhere, Mama.
>> We're tap-dancing.
>> There you go.
>> There you go, Alicia.
>> PROBST: Alicia's in first.
Shii Ann scores one for Mogo
Mogo.
Mogo Mogo: 1; Chapera: zip.
Next matchup:
Rupert versus Ethan.
Foot in the black.
Start spinning.
>> Come on, Rupert.
>> PROBST: Rupert with his
boots.
Rupert first in.
(cheering)
Mogo Mogo: 2; Chapera: 0.
Jenna and Kathy...
start spinning.
Kathy in.
Jenna scores for Chapera.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: 2-1, Mogo Mogo leads.
It's Lex versus Boston Rob.
Start spinning.
Boston Rob working it.
Lex reacting.
Lex staying on.
Lex first in.
Boston Rob scores for Chapera.
We're tied 2-2.
Jerri versus Amber.
Start spinning.
>> Come on, Amber.
Better balance.
>> PROBST: Amber looking very
confident.
>> Run, run, run, run, run.
>> PROBST: Up and going.
Jerri-- first in.
Amber scores for Chapera.
>> Amber, nicely done.
>> PROBST: Chapera leads 3-2
after the first cycle.
We're going to randomly draw new
numbers, get new matchups.
Here's where we're at:
Chapera 3; Mogo Mogo 2.
First tribe to five wins reward.
Once again, it is Shii Ann and
Alicia.
Foot in the black.
Start spinning.
>> Come on, Alicia.
>> PROBST: Alicia first in.
Shii Ann scores for Mogo Mogo.
We're tied 3-3.
Ethan versus Boston Rob.
>> Come on, Rob.
>> PROBST: Best matchup so far.
>> Wow.
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
Yes!
>> Amber, this is you.
>> Amber, cut me some slack.
>> PROBST: Kathy versus Amber.
>> Let's go, Amber.
>> PROBST: Here's where things
stand: Chapera leads 4-3.
If Amber wins, she wins reward
for Chapera.
>> Come on, Amber.
>> PROBST: Foot in the black.
Start spinning.
>> Don't let go.
Don't let go.
>> PROBST: Kathy first in.
Amber wins reward for Chapera.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, here's how
it's going to work: later today
Jenna, since she was the
representative, will return to
Mogo Mogo and help herself to
the three items.
Grill, one bag of rice and the
Hawaiian sling.
Nice challenge, guys.
Head back to camp.
>> You know, when you think
about it, who wouldn't be a
little anxious to be getting a
visit by somebody from the
opposing tribe to take some of
your most valuable items away.
>> It'll be so pleasant.
We have everything ready for
her; she doesn't feel like
we're hostile.
>> Took a little punch in
the jaw, and now, you know,
we're just shaking our...
shaking our head with the
thought and the prospect of
losing... you know, our fishing
spear's a way that we gather
food every day, and, you know,
as if that weren't enough, it's
a bit of a one-two punch with
the rice as well.
>> Knock-knock.
>> Hey.
>> Hello.
>> How you doing?
>> Good.
>> We have it all set up
for you over here.
>> I have something for
you guys.
>> Oh, what do you have?
>> Um, we brought you
bar soap and toilet paper,
and a little scrub brush to
brush your clothes, and a
toothbrush.
Something to clean you up.
>> Thank you so much, Jenna.
>> Here's our grill
and our fishing rod for you.
>> Okay.
It's not my fault, and it's not
even our fault that we had to
take things from their camp.
This is a game, and they know
that.
So it was nice that I brought
something over to them to say,
like, "I'm very sorry that you
guys don't have these things,
and I have to take more from
you."
>> We were wondering
if you would be kind enough to
give us a couple of scoops of
rice from our bag.
Because we lost a lot of our
rice to mildew in the beginning,
and we've been really rationing
for, you know, a rainy day.
>> Okay.
>> And...
>> What do you have exactly?
You have one full bag, and...?
>> One full bag and
like a fourth of the other bag.
I was wondering if you would be
kind enough to give us...
>> Yes, of course.
>> ...a couple of...
>> We've been so diligent
about rationing our rice, which
at this point, you know...
hindsight is 20-20 and you don't
know what's going to happen, but
you're almost kicking yourself
because we were eating only as
much as we needed to make it
last longer and now we just
lost, you know, the lion's share
of what we had.
>> Thank you, Jenna.
>> No, we're not trying
to wipe you out.
It was just what we needed,
so...
>> And you got the grade-A rice.
>> Yes. Thank you so much.
The vibe is down.
I don't care what they're saying
when we come to immunity
challenges, they are down.
They know... they're trying to
smile, they're trying to be
nice, but they're not happy.
They're slowly losing everything
they have.
They're not happy.
>> They ain't got a whole
hell of a lot over there to get.
>> We got the biggest stuff
they have.
>> We got everything.
We won everything.
This whole game, this whole game
is about Chapera kicking ass.
>> I'm going real slow so
I don't drop anything.
Oh, my tribe was psyched when I
came back with the loot.
I have rice, and Rupert just
never put down that Hawaiian
sling.
>> We're going to sharpen them
points down to a...
Oh, my God.
I've been waiting 20 days to not
have to poke fish with a stick.
I'm going to be the hunter
tomorrow.
I hope I see that big six-foot
shark.
I hope I see that yellowfin
tuna.
I hope I see that grouper that's
this big.
>> I know you're excited.
>> Oh, my gosh, I'm excited.
>> I'm excited, too.
>> I've made ten different
spears trying to get
that damn thing.
>> Today is definitely
one of the best days for me.
The fact that we're getting more
rice, eating more, helped out
great in the challenge.
And it's just ended up being a
really good day.
>> Right.
(laughter)
Everybody has gas every now
and again.
Especially in this situation.
You see the abuse?
You see that, Jenna?
That's grounds for
"I'll see ya later."
>> If Rob and Amber are
not playing kissy face, sucky,
kissy face yet, they are going
to be soon.
Um, I have walked up on them in
the middle in the night where
they just looked so guilty it's
not even funny, and I know
something's going on.
>> Later on we'll take a
walk, all right?
>> Definitely at first I
was stringing him along.
The flirting was a huge strategy
in the beginning.
Um, but then I got caught up in
it, and feelings, you know,
emerged.
(laughing, talking indistinctly)
>> Amber is slammin'.
She's sweet, she's beautiful,
she's funny, she's got a great
personality.
Her ass is smokin', too.
>> It's crazy because
coming into this game I never
expected in a million years for
this to ever happen.
And actually, I told myself that
I wouldn't really let something
like this happen, but... I love
having the comfort level of it,
and I love... I love that he,
you know, keeps me warm at night
and he, you know, makes me feel
safe out here.
I can vent to him, complain to
him about anything and he won't
hold it against me.
You're not ever supposed to feel
secure in this game, but with
Rob and I, I feel 99.9% secure.
>> Amber and I have been
fooling around a little bit out
here.
I mean, it's all in good fun.
I'm definitely attracted to her.
It'd be nice to have a million
dollars and take the girl away,
too.
Much better, much better.
Good night.
>> Good night.
(thunder roaring)
>> We might have a rough
one today, boys.
It's pouring right there.
>> I'm gonna get fish
before it starts storming again.
>> Yeah.
>> Rupert's all excited
about having the Hawaiian sling.
You know, it's his baby.
Now he can catch a fish...
(imitating Rupert) and show
how much he's worth to the
tribe.
That's his whole life is that
spear.
First of all, the guy looks like
Grizzly Adams, but he thinks
he's Aqua Man in the ocean.
This guy talks baby talk.
What is that?
You ever notice that?
(imitating Rupert) "My name
is Rupert.
I'm a big and strong fisherman
in the Pearl Islands."
Now that we got the spear, we
don't need him.
(chuckles)
I'm not sure that we ever did.
And he comes back with a bag of
fish feeling all good about
himself.
(chuckling)
>> My God, it took all I
had to stop.
>> Is that the 20-pounder
you were talking about?
>> Uh-huh.
(laughing)
>> I know just as well as
anybody else, if you got a
Hawaiian sling, it's like
basically going to the pet store
and grabbing one of the goldfish
containers and just picking out
which fish you want.
Wow, look... Rupert.
>> Hey, I don't think I'll
take that spear away.
>> I'm afraid I'm going to
be embarrassed now.
(chuckling)
>> Man, there's a shark
that I was looking at like this.
I wanted it.
(laughs)
>> ROB (yells): Yeah!
>> I'm just glad he
caught a fish.
>> Going back down.
>> Okay.
>> I proceeded to go into
the water and catch 11 fish
myself.
The city kid from Boston with
the Hawaiian sling versus Aqua
Man.
I'm going to need a boat to tow
this one in.
I've never seen anything that
big before.
>> Sometimes I really
like Boston Rob...
>> Boston style.
>> Other times I see kind of an
arrogant pain in the ass.
>> He got a couple fish.
>> Very good.
You know, he wants to be the
man.
>> I think Rupert was
shocked when he saw that I
brought back so many fish.
I think it made him realize that
we can use Rupert or the
Hawaiian sling.
A Hawaiian sling doesn't need
any rice.
So Rupert's stock just went down
about 20 points.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
All right, first things first.
Boston Rob.
Immunity back up for grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
we're going to test your skills
with a variety of weapons.
Along the way, you will earn
arrows that you will use in the
final round.
First round: blow gun.
Each tribe member will get one
chance.
At the end of the round, the
tribe who's closest to the
center of the target earns two
arrows.
Losing tribe earns one arrow.
Second round: you will throw a
spear with the same result.
The tribe that's closest to the
center earns two more arrows.
Losing tribe earns one arrow.
For the final round, you will
take the arrows you've earned
and select one tribe member to
be your archer.
They will fire arrows at the
final target.
Closest to the center of the
target wins immunity for their
tribe.
If you win immunity, you are
guaranteed a one-in-ten shot at
being the sole survivor.
Big stakes.
Chapera, you have one extra
member.
Cannot sit out the same person
in back-to-back challenges.
Big Tom sat out yesterday.
Who's sitting out today?
>> Okay, I'll sit out.
>> PROBST: All right, Alicia
will have a spot on the bench.
Everybody else wait for my go.
All right, first round-- blow
guns.
We've randomly drew numbers.
Chapera will fire first.
Jenna.
>> Put her in the red.
>> PROBST: The end of the round,
the tribe who is closest to the
center of the target earns two
arrows.
>> That's it, Jenna.
Nice and relaxed.
>> PROBST: Jenna, deflects off
the target.
No hit.
Mogo Mogo.
Jerri.
First shot for Mogo Mogo.
Jerri connects.
Mogo Mogo first on the board.
Next up for Chapera.
Amber.
Just not enough wind for Amber.
(chuckling)
Shii Ann trying to better
Jerri's mark.
Shii Ann just short of the
target.
Boston Rob.
Trying to get Chapera on the
board.
Boston Rob misses wide to the
right.
Chapera still not on the board.
Kathy up for Mogo Mogo.
(laughs)
Kathy just shy of the target.
Mogo Mogo still with the mark to
beat.
Rupert doesn't connect.
Challenge proving more difficult
than we thought.
Ethan far short of the target.
Big Tom, the last shot for
Chapera.
That's the mark to beat, Big
Tom, or Mogo Mogo wins.
>> Come on, Big Tom.
>> PROBST: Big Tom can't do it.
With one connection, Jerri wins.
Mogo Mogo earns two arrows,
Chapera one.
Moving to the next round.
(cheering)
After the first round, Mogo Mogo
with two arrows.
Chapera with one.
It's time for spear tossing.
Mogo Mogo's up first.
Trying to get closest to the
center of the target, Jerri.
Just left.
>> Good try, Jerri.
>> PROBST: Chapera, you're up.
And he does.
Nice shot.
Close.
Chapera still with the mark to
beat.
Kathy up for Mogo Mogo.
>> (sighs): Oh.
>> Good try, Kathy.
>> PROBST: Big Tom up for
Chapera.
No messing around.
Not better than what Rupert put
up.
Ethan up for Mogo Mogo.
Nice shot.
Not quite inside of Rupert's.
Boston Rob for Chapera.
Nice shot.
Not enough.
Comes down to the last shot for
Mogo Mogo.
Lex.
Two more arrows at stake, Lex.
Got to get inside Rupert's toss,
which means you have to be in
the yellow.
Nope, just outside.
Chapera wins.
Both tribes move into the final
round with three arrows.
>> Nice job, Rupert.
>> PROBST: Moving into the final
round, each tribe has three
arrows.
You need to select your archers.
Chapera, who's it going to be?
Boston Rob.
For Mogo Mogo?
Jerri.
Rock, paper, scissors to see who
shoots first.
Rock, paper... you want to go
last, I assume?
>> You go first.
>> PROBST: Jerri's up first for
Mogo Mogo.
You'll each have three arrows.
Closest to the target wins
immunity for your tribe.
Jerri, any experience with a bow
and arrow?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Jerri misses just to
the right.
Boston Rob up for Chapera.
>> Come on, Rob.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob, any
previous experience with a bow
and arrow?
>> Uh, my brother is a bow
hunter.
Tried to teach me a little bit
before I left.
>> Come on, Rob.
>> PROBST: Just to the left.
Jerri shooting her second arrow.
Misses just to the right.
Jerri down to her last arrow.
Boston Rob with his second
arrow.
Still nobody has hit the target.
Boston Rob on the target.
Not a great shot, but you are on
the board.
Jerri with the last shot for
Mogo Mogo.
>> You got it, Jerri.
>> PROBST: This is your last
arrow, Jerri.
You've got to get inside Rob's
hit.
A lot of pressure.
You don't get inside Rob's hit,
Tribal Council tonight for Mogo
Mogo.
Somebody being voted out.
Wide to the right.
That's it.
Chapera wins immunity.
Mogo Mogo heading to Tribal
Council.
Chapera, once again, immunity
going back to camp with you.
Congratulations.
Safe from the vote.
Mogo Mogo, not as good news for
you.
Jerri stepped up into a make-or-
break position.
Didn't work out.
You look frustrated.
>> JERRI (drily): Really.
I wonder why.
>> PROBST: The result is Tribal
Council tonight.
Somebody's going home.
I'll see you there.
You can head back to camp.
>> I'm just... I'm really
sorry, you guys.
>> It happens.
>> Don't beat yourself up.
>> I know, I'm trying not
to, but it's hard.
>> Don't beat yourself up.
Let's just get the fire going.
>> It's just hard not to.
>> Is the fire on still?
>> We need a monsoon here.
>> I don't want to go to
Tribal Council.
>> But we got...
>> I'm pissed because I
stuck my neck out.
And I blew it.
I blew it.
I've lost the immunity challenge
for everybody today.
The disappointment mixed with my
fear of being blamed and voted
out tonight is just...
overwhelming me.
>> (whispers): You talked
to Kathy already, right?
>> Not that much.
>> So we're going to...
tonight we're going to...
we're going to take Ethan out.
I think that strategically it
just makes the most sense now.
Do you agree?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, he's just...
>> I'm just... Yeah.
I'm just glad it's not me.
>> Not you.
>> But if for some reason...
>> No, it's... no.
No, no, no, no.
That's just completely just...
don't even talk about it 'cause
he may try to pull a Hail Mary
move of some sort, and it's just
not worth it for us.
We can stay in this game.
You don't need to ask me about
it, but it's Ethan tonight.
>> Okay.
>> I won't say another word.
>> All right.
Um, he's just... he's a charmer.
>> Yeah.
>> He's a nice guy.
Um... it's dangerous.
Ethan and I came into this game
with a bit of a handicap, and
that is that we have not just,
you know... we're not just
acquaintances outside the game.
We're good friends.
I knew that the last thing he
wanted to have happen to him in
this game was to be blindsided
and to get voted out without
knowing about it ahead of time.
And I think the honorable thing
to do here was to tell him when
it was going to happen.
I've got my own agenda this
time; I've got my own plan.
It doesn't include him.
I can't afford ballast; I can't
afford dead weight; and I
certainly can't be dragging an
ex-winner along with me just
because he's my friend.
This isn't Africa.
This is All-Star.
There are two things I need to
talk to you about.
I mean, one is the game.
And one is our friendship.
And the two things... and I know
it's hard for you at this point
to see how one can, you know,
somehow exist separate from the
other, but I'm going to try to
make you understand how it has
to be that way.
Um, I think that at this point,
it's just, it's better for my
game if we vote you out tonight.
But it has nothing to do
with friendship.
This is business.
Strictly business.
And I have to play the game
differently this time around,
because the first time around,
I lost.
>> You have to play...
Lex, as much as you say you want
it, this is business, it's not.
>> It's not easy for me to
tell you this 'cause I know how
disappointing this is.
Am I having fun doing this? No.
Am I taking pleasure in telling
you this? No.
In fact, this is horrible.
But I wanted... I wanted to talk
to you about this 'cause I
didn't want to blindside you,
and I didn't think that it was
right, I didn't think it was
fair, and I didn't think it was
cool.
And I know... that it's a major
drag for you to go out of the
game for Jerri, and I
understand that.
>> She's done nothing for
this game; she's done nothing
for this tribe; she's done
nothing for you; and you're
rewarding her with it.
She does not deserve to be here.
She didn't lift a finger over
there.
>> That's why.
She's not much of a threat.
>> But she does not
deserve to be here.
>> I know that.
>> She does not deserve to be
here.
>> Sorry.
And, dude, I'm sorry.
>> Don't apologize.
What pisses me off the most is,
if they think Jerri more worthy
to stay in this game than I am,
then... that there's something
wrong with their screws in their
head, and I don't know what game
they're playing.
Lex is like...
I told Lex, you know, Jerri
doesn't deserve to be here,
all that smack.
He's, like, "That's little stuff
to me."
He's, like, "I don't care."
He's, like, "I'll deal with
that."
Jerri's a vote I can... I can
pull her along and get rid of
her whenever I want.
She'll do anything I say.
That's... (grunts)
(growls)
>> I know, I know.
>> And she's gonna get
further than you...
>> No.
>> She might.
There's no rhyme or reason of
how Lex is playing this game.
There'll be no sense of security
with Lex at any time.
I mean, he told me that.
I mean, he told me that over
there, 'cause that's why he's
voting me off.
>> When I talked to Ethan,
and I looked into his eyes,
you know, I truly would love
to bring him with us.
He is a nice guy.
He has a big heart.
(whispering): I do not believe
he'll bring me along for very
long.
Because I don't trust anybody
in this game.
But I don't want to take Lex out
before Jerri.
>> No.
>> It would be Jerri tonight.
All right.
>> So I'll vote for Jerri,
and then you and she can
talk about it, and I'll...
I'm a gambler.
>> I'm leaning towards you,
believe me.
I don't know, there's something,
again, about looking into
Ethan's eyes and also looking
into Lex's eyes.
There is a moment that you need
to trust and have loyalty in
this game.
You've got to.
There is no way I want Jerri in
the final four.
I just don't want her around.
I want somebody, truly, that
plays the game well, but also
works.
I want somebody with bug bites
on them and scratches and their
fingers are gnarled.
I'm sorry.
It's just the way I am.
I've been thinking about it, but
the sun's going down.
I don't have much time.
>> PROBST: Hello, guys.
Day 21.
Let's talk about today's
challenge.
Jerri, you ended up in the hero-
or-goat role, depending on how
it came out.
Was that your choice?
Were you elected?
Was it random?
>> I volunteered, um,
because I do have archery
experience, and... my tribe
trusted and believed in me,
and I let them down.
I apologize profusely.
So regardless of the outcome, I
feel good about it.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann, is there a
little bit of relief when
somebody else steps up and says,
"I'll take that role," knowing
that at least you can't be the
goat?
>> Today Jerri volunteered.
I believed her.
We all believed her, and
unfortunately, we lost.
But that could have happened
with anyone.
>> PROBST: Kathy, would Jerri be
thinking irrationally if she was
a little worried that maybe
tonight that challenge is gonna
come back to haunt her?
>> You know, I'm sure
she's concerned about it.
You know, it'd be under my skin
if I stepped forward like that.
Especially now, when things are
dwindling.
You know, it's human nature.
I'm sure she's concerned.
>> PROBST: Ethan, has it crossed
your mind that you're the last
remaining previous winner in
this game?
>> Yeah, it has.
I like that.
I'm proud of the way I played,
and I'm happy that I'm still
here.
>> PROBST: What about you is the
biggest threat to the other four
sitting here tonight?
>> I think, uh, I'm a
threat to these other four
because, uh, I'm a winner.
But in addition to that, that's
something they should look into,
saying, "Well, that's an
advantage as well."
No one's gonna vote for a winner
in the final two, Jeff.
Principle alone, no one wants to
see a winner win again.
>> PROBST: Lex, you kind of...
had a weird reaction to that.
>> I don't think that's
necessarily true.
In fact, if I was on the jury,
and if that winner was shrewd
enough to just make a good,
pointed argument that,
"You know what?
I came into this game with the
biggest target on my back.
None of you figured I could ever
get this far, and the fact that,
even against all odds, I made it
to the final two," I'd have a
hard time picking reasons not to
vote him to win because that
guy made it against all odds.
>> PROBST: Tough game.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Touch decisions.
>> PROBST: It is time to vote.
Shii Ann, you're up.
>> Jerri, um, today you took
my life into your hands
and you blew it.
I feel you've not played the
game well; I feel you've not
worked hard enough; and I think
you should be voted off.
>> It's really, really easy
to win with grace and dignity,
but it's much harder to lose
with that same grace and
dignity.
Let's see how you do.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
E.Z. Ethan.
Jerri.
One vote Jerri, one vote Ethan.
Ethan.
That's two votes Ethan,
one vote Jerri.
Eighth person voted out of the
tribe...
Ethan. Three's enough votes.
You need to bring me your torch.
Ethan, the tribe has spoken.
>> Have fun. Play hard.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
>> PROBST: Well, you've made it
21 days.
With 18 days left, trust will
become the single most valuable
resource in this game, and the
most difficult thing to find.
See how it plays out.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> Being on a losing team
all the time--
it's just depressing.
>> PROBST: The gap between the
tribes couldn't be wider.
>> We was just tickled to death.
>> PROBST: But while everyone
is talking merge...
>> I'm ready for a merge.
I'm ready for all of us to be
one tribe.
>> PROBST: ...what happens next
will turn their world upside
down.
Drop your buffs.
>> I feel like I'm the one
who got screwed in this
whole situation.
>> I do have some solace
in knowing that, uh, I played
the game my way.
Tonight I had no control over
what happened.
You know, I fought to the bitter
end, and I got further than any
other winner, and I'm extremely
proud of that, and I wouldn't
trade any of this experience.
I'll treasure this for the rest
of my life.
Thank you.