>> JEFF PROBST: 21 Days ago, 18
former castaways returned to
play the ultimate game one more
time.
They were split into three
tribes and marooned with only
one machete.
It was the least amount of
supplies ever given to a group
of survivors.
Their experience and their
eagerness to prove that they
were the best of the best set
the stage for one of the most
cutthroat Survivor adventures
ever.
All aspects of the game were
escalated.
The conflict...
>> I'm not yelling.
I'm just saying, call it like it
is.
>> I am calling it like
it is.
We just talked about it.
( thunder rumbling )
>> PROBST: The emotion...
>> It's not worth it.
>> PROBST: ...and the struggle
to survive.
>> Shark bite!
>> He was not letting
go.
He was never letting go.
>> PROBST: Tonight, in a special
episode, we'll take a closer
look at the first 21 days of
Survivor All-Stars through a
series of highlights...
>> Due to someone who
is very ill at home right now, I
need to pull myself out of the
game.
>> PROBST: ...and
never-before-seen footage.
>> We all decided to be
Saboga, who was going to Tribal
Council that night.
And we had a blast.
>> All of you Survivor
All-Stars, I think it is time
to vote.
>> My vote is for Jerri!
>> Homey's walking funny
because he has a small problem
of chafing going on.
>> And now he's walking
more and more hobbled as the
days go by.
( laughs )
>> Things down in the
nether regions have become a bit
chapped.
It hurts.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> PROBST: On day one, under
full military escort, the 18
all-stars began the most
competitive Survivor to date.
>> It's never been done
before.
No one has ever gone back to
play this game twice.
We know how bad it gets, and we
know how long this road is.
>> This ain't a little
boy's game.
This is for the big boys.
>> All-Star Survivor is
going to be so cutthroat, it's
not even going to be funny.
Nobody trusts anybody, you
understand?
>> PROBST: For the first time,
there were three tribes--
Chapera, Mogo Mogo and Saboga.
When the tribes arrived at their
beaches, they found only a
machete and a map to their water
hole.
>> Oh, nice!
>> We did find our water
source, but we can't drink it
right out of the well.
There's potential brain
parasites that will put you in a
coma.
>> PROBST: The water had to be
boiled, but starting a fire with
no supplies bordered on the
impossible.
>> That's it.
>> Come on!
Come on!
>> I did it for two days in
Borneo.
I can't do fire.
I have tried.
>> All right.
There's that positive attitude
we're looking for.
>> I'm running out of
steam.
>> Yeah, I think I
could start the fire without
even blinking, but they don't
need to know that.
( laughs )
>> PROBST: In the midst of the
struggle for fire at Saboga...
( Rupert sighs )
>> My head's ready to
pop.
>> PROBST: ...Rudy struck a deal
with Rupert.
>> I think, uh, me and you
ought to think about an
alliance.
>> You're a man of your
word, too, from what I know of
you.
>> Yeah.
I, uh, figured me and Rupert
ought to protect ourselves and
form an alliance, and that's
what we did.
>> You and I are going
to be strong to the end.
( Rudy speaks quietly )
>> PROBST: At Chapera, it was
Boston Rob and Amber who were
making a connection.
>> So, what do you
think?
You want to make an alliance?
Cover our own asses?
>> I don't know if I can
take you seriously or not.
>> I'm being 100%
serious.
Amber and I have an alliance,
for obvious reasons.
She's beautiful.
Any idiot can see that.
>> PROBST: While Rob and Amber's
alliance seemed to be made from
the heart, Rob's alliance with
Big Tom was all business.
>> You watch my back,
Tom, I'll watch yours, all
right?
>> Me and Rob's got a
little alliance.
No, I don't trust him.
Hell, no.
But I don't trust none of 'em,
and, uh, if Rob will hang in
there with me, we can pull this
thing through.
>> It's humid, huh?
Big Tom wants to make an
alliance with me.
He wants to stay tight with me,
you know?
I got my thing going with Amber.
I got Big Tom on the side.
I think in his eyes it's a
primary alliance.
In mine, it's secondary.
But he doesn't need to know
that.
Not until the time comes.
>> PROBST: At the first
three-way immunity challenge...
Survivors, ready!
>> Here we go, here we
go.
>> PROBST: Go!
...Saboga fell behind early and
never recovered.
>> Come on, guys, get
me over there.
>> PROBST: And Chapera and Mogo
Mogo shared immunity.
Chapera, Mogo Mogo,
congratulations.
Safe from Tribal Council and out
here at least three more days.
( cheering )
Having dodged the first Tribal
Council, Chapera decided to
create one of their own.
>> Come on in.
First, from Survivor one, Rudy
Boesch.
Next, the winner from Survivor
Africa, Ethan Zohn.
From Survivor Pearl Islands,
Rupert.
From Survivor Australia, Jerri
Manthey.
There's Jerri.
>> I just want to pour
some hot chocolate over some hot
guy's bod.
>> The winner from
Survivor Australia, Tina
Wesson.
And from Survivor Borneo, Jenna
Lewis.
>> Oh, I'm so glad to be
here, everybody!
Oh! Jeff, Jeff!
Oh, Jeff, oh.
>> Let's settle down.
>> We all decided to be
Saboga, who was going to Tribal
Council that night.
And we had a blast doing it.
>> Here we are, day three.
All of you "Survivor All-Stars."
What's going on? Jerri?
>> What... what is
happening here?
I don't deserve this.
The last time I played
Survivor, we were pretty
serious, but everybody here is a
comedian.
There is not one person who's
not.
>> Rupert, you've been
here for Survivor: Pearl
Islands.
Three months later, you're now
back here in Survivor: Pearl
Islands.
>> The only reason I
come back, someone messed with
the handlebar of my....
>> I didn't touch your
spear, Rupert.
I never touched your spear.
>> ( growling ): Rudy!
>> Come on!
>> How's my hair, Jeff?
I played Ethan because I just
wanted to give him a hard time
and let everybody realize how
ridiculous he looks with his
little jheri curls.
>> I think it is time to
vote.
>> My vote is for holy
roller Tina.
She stabbed me in the back once.
She's not going to do it again.
Tina.
>> Jenna, I'm sorry to
have to vote for you.
It's just a game.
Sorry, babe.
>> ( In Southern
accent ): Lord, please forgive
me for my language that I am
about to use right now, but Miss
Jerri Manthey, I am voting for
you.
You were a bitch the first time
on Survivor Australia and
three years hasn't done you any
good.
You're still a bitch.
My vote is for Jerri!
>> I thought everybody
was funny at Tribal Council from
Amber playing Tina to Rob
playing Jeff Probst.
I mean, the kid's obviously
watched a couple Survivors.
He's got him down pat.
>> Jenna, the tribe has
spoken.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> See y'all.
( all imitating theme song )
( imitates soundtrack chanting )
( thunder crashing )
>> PROBST: But the real Tribal
Council was no joke for the
losing Saboga tribe.
During a downpour, the stigma of
being a former winner was too
much for Tina to overcome and
she was the first person voted
out of Survivor All-Stars.
Tina, the tribe has spoken.
>> TINA: I knew early on that I
was in trouble.
You know, there was only one
other winner, and I knew that
they would keep Ethan as the
stronger one.
But what a mistake it would be
to not even play the game.
So that's why I came back, and
it's been a blast.
>> PROBST: On day four, Colby
was dealing with a delicate
situation.
>> Colby's walking funny
because he has a small problem
of chafing going on.
I think he has chafed the inner
side of his inner thigh.
>> And now he's walking
more and more hobbled as the
days go by.
( laughing )
>> A true Texan at heart
never complains.
>> Yeah, things down in
the nether regions have become a
bit chapped.
My gait, if you will, is my
attempt to get a little air flow
going in there and hopefully
with a little time, everything
is going to heal.
But that's the only way I can
get relief, is just being as
bowlegged as a bull rider who
just stepped off a 3,000-pound
nightmare.
It hurts something fierce.
>> PROBST: Later on day four, a
mysterious box with three locks
arrived at tree mail.
>> Anything at this point
that you get to open is fun
because it's like a gift.
>> PROBST: In a grueling reward
challenge, Ethan carried Saboga
to their first victory.
>> PROBST: Saboga wins reward!
But with the reward,
Saboga faced a tough decision.
Each tribe today received a
lockbox.
I'll tell you what is in the
Rice.
The only problem is that lockbox
and the rice in it does you
no good because you need three
keys to get it open.
And even if you had it open,
without fire, you can't cook the
rice.
So here's the offer.
If you take the pot with the
clue and the map and the flint
instead of the blankets, Mogo
Mogo gets it as well as Chapera.
>> Give everybody a
chance.
( cheers )
>> PROBST: With flint, the
tribes finally got fire.
>> Whoa.
>> We got fire!
Yay!
>> PROBST: With the struggle for
fire behind them, the members of
Chapera turned their attention
to other problems, like
understanding Big Tom.
>> Hey, we ain't got a good
mate among us.
>> You guys get that?
>> No.
>> Big Tom?
Who knows his language?
He's a huge comic relief.
I love sitting back and just
listening to Big Tom, even if I
don't understand anything he
says.
>> So anyway, baby doll may
want to go over and make a big
glob of love and I tell her...
>> We need a translator
on that one.
That was just a little too much.
>> I have no clue what
you just said.
All I heard was "gob of love."
>> Big Tom is by far
worst.
I mean, half the time nobody
knows what he is saying.
>> There's plenty...
>> Huh?
>> I said there's plenty
right there.
>> What?
>> I said there's plenty
over there.
>> Where:
>> Over by them rocks.
Snails.
They sittin' right there.
>> Yeah, there's plenty
of them.
I'm telling you, this guy, half
the time he talks, I just go
"yesum, uh-huh."
You got to have a special degree
to be able to speak Big Tom.
( mumbling )
"What?"
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge on day six...
Survivors, ready?
Go!
...the tribes had to raise boats
from the ocean floor and race to
the finish.
Chapera takes the lead.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Chapera cruised to
first place, Mogo Mogo's
determination kept them going,
and Saboga's hopes for immunity
sank completely along with their
boat.
Chapera first to cross.
Wins immunity!
Mogo Mogo wins immunity.
For the second straight time,
Saboga going to Tribal Council.
Back at the Saboga camp, Rupert
vowed to stay true to his
alliance with Rudy.
>> Rudy came to me on
the first day saying, "I need a
buddy."
>> I know what you're
saying.
I adore him, but we're losing
bad.
>> I am not writing
Rudy's name down.
I know that.
I'm not writing Rudy's name
down.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
despite Rupert's loyalty, the
former Navy Seal was the second
person voted out of Survivor
All-Stars.
Rudy, the tribe has spoken.
>> Jenna, she kept edging
me on right to two hours before
they eliminated me.
She shouldn't have done that.
I wish I would have lasted
longer.
I'm going to keep doing this
until I win.
>> PROBST: On day seven, Richard
got up close and personal with a
shark.
>> I let the head part
go for a second, and whoop!
Shark bite!
And I poke him in the eyes.
He takes another chunk deeper.
There was no way-- he was not
letting go.
He was never letting go.
So I swam to get on a rock and
pound the side of his head with
a rock until he lets go.
Ee-yai-yai-yai-yai.
>> Oh, my God.
>> His teeth?
Right there.
>> SUSAN: Oh, my God.
>> He's got me,
pulling.
The hell if you're going to stay
on my arm.
It's like this.
>> Is it possible to call
a gay man a stud?
>> It's like man
verses nature.
So Hemingway-esque.
I love it.
>> PROBST: At tree mail, the
tribes received a welcomed
surprise.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: The challenge was to
build the best possible shelter
in 24 hours.
The reward would be a gift of
comfort items dropped from the
sky.
Boston Rob used his construction
expertise and took the reins at
Chapera, and Amber quickly took
notice.
>> I'll admit when I saw
him building that shelter... he
was pretty hot building that
shelter.
He is good at doing what he
does.
It is getting much easier and
easier to flirt with Boston Rob.
>> PROBST: at Mogo Mogo, Jenna's
mind just wasn't in the
challenge.
>> There's a lot of
other factors that come into my
game that may not come into
anybody else's game, like my
mom.
She's had cancer for a long time
and she's not better.
And I'm just afraid she might
pass away while I'm here.
>> PROBST: And at Saboga, Rupert
and Jerri clashed over Rupert's
log cabin design.
>> We are going to dig
down into the sand a couple feet
to add to our height so when you
walk into it, you'll be able to
stand up.
And that's what I want.
>> Rupert's a complete
control freak.
He has to have everything his
way.
He thinks he's the only one who
can do it right.
>> PROBST: As day turned to
night, it became apparent that
Rupert was digging Saboga's
grave.
>> Rupert's idea was a
little ambitious.
We ended up working all through
the night.
>> Not good.
>> My God, I could not
believe the stupidity.
This is Rupert gone mad.
>> PROBST: On day eight, a local
contractor visited each beach to
determine a winner.
I brought along with me Rafa,
an expert in construction.
Take a look.
At Mogo Mogo, things got off to
a shaky start.
>> Rafa-- he starts going
around the shelter and the first
thing he does is start grabbing
on to things, jerking them,
trying to rip them down.
I don't know that Rafa realizes,
we have to live in the shelter.
>> PROBST: And at Chapera,
things stood on solid ground.
>> You're not moving this.
>> This is three foot in
the ground, and that... all this
is square.
>> PROBST: Ready?
Vámanos?
>> Vámanos.
>> PROBST: When the contractor
saw Rupert's underground
shelter, Saboga's hopes of
winning seemed all washed up.
>> Saboga? Oh...
>> PROBST: You don't like...?
>> No, no, no.
>> PROBST: It's dangerous?
>> Yeah.
This is the... the water...
>> And then I see him
tell Jeff, "Water go down in.
Bad."
>> PROBST: Chapera once again
came out on top.
Their reward for having the best
shelter included blankets, a
mattress and wine.
>> We've never been so
excited in our lives.
That was just a pinnacle moment.
>> PROBST: The mood at Mogo Mogo
was not so cheerful.
Jenna Morasca was contemplating
quitting altogether.
>> Well, I just want to let
you guys know there are a lot of
things I thought I would be able
to overcome here, but my mom is
really ill.
I don't think I'd ever
forgive myself if I knew that I
was here playing a game and
something happened to her.
>> PROBST: When the tribes
arrived for the immunity
challenge,
Jenna made her decision.
>> Due to someone who
is very ill at home right now, I
need to pull myself out of the
game.
>> PROBST: I just want to
understand exactly why you're
leaving.
>> She's my mother,
and I should be there in case
something happens.
I love this game, but it's my
family.
>> PROBST: Let's bring in the
boat.
>> PROBST: Jenna, we're thinking
about you.
>> Thanks. Bye, guys.
Have fun.
>> PROBST: Jenna Morasca became
the second person ever to walk
away from the game.
But her instincts were right.
Eight days later, her mom lost
her battle with cancer with
Jenna by her side.
Night nine brought one of the
worst storms in Survivor
history.
>> We need a boat.
Mayday, mayday, mayday.
>> We have constructed a
shelter that is pretty
unbelievable.
>> The shelter held up
pretty good.
I slept almost all night long
because I was under the blanket,
warm, and I just slept the whole
night.
>> PROBST: Well, almost the
whole night.
>> You're so warm.
>> Boston Rob and Amber
are going to do it.
I don't know when, but they're
going to do it.
>> PROBST: Things weren't so
cozy at Saboga.
Their underground shelter failed
miserably.
>> The stupid shelter
that I built was destroyed.
Digging into the sand is the
dumbest idea I've ever had in my
life, and we paid dearly tonight
for it.
>> The rain just started
pouring and the whole shelter
filled up with water.
This never would have happened
if they hadn't dug that hole.
It's not worth it.
>> PROBST: the next morning,
emotionally and physically
spent, Saboga realized they were
back to square one.
>> The plan today is we
got to make shelter, we've got
to make fire and we've got to
get it together now.
>> PROBST: But once again, Jerri
was on the outs with her tribe.
>> When we were deciding
where to rebuild our shelter for
the third time, Jerri wanted
nothing to do with it.
>> Oh, come on, you
gotta help.
>> She's had enough, you
know.
Check out.
>> Once they started
working on the actual building
process, that's when I felt it
was necessary for me to speak
up.
You're going to put those on top
of the bamboo, uh, the palms,
right?
It needs to go on top, 'cause
otherwise the palms clog it up
and acts as a... whoosh, instead
of a whoosh.
>> You want to really
keep it waterproof.
If you want to put it on top,
I don't care.
I just think with as many palms
as we have, we're only going to
get a foot and a half, two feet.
>> Jenna says put the
bamboo on.
Jerri says no, don't put the
bamboo on and then cops this big
old attitude with me about we
can't discuss anything.
We always just gotta do it your
way.
Well, one of you says the bamboo
is going under and of you one
says the bamboo's going over.
>> Well, that's what
happens when you discuss two
different views.
>> Why can't I say
discuss it?
>> Because it's obvious
that's what's gonna happen.
>> I was very fond of
Jerri.
I thought we were getting along
great until we got the challenge
of building a new shelter.
A little bit of conflict and now
I'm the devil.
It makes me feel inadequate when
the girl won't even look at me.
She will have nothing to do with
me right now.
That does make me uncomfortable.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
On Day Ten, Chapera continued
their victory roll when they won
a Survivor style bathroom, as
well as a clue to the final key
to their lock box.
Take a shower, get cleaned up.
You guys can head back to camp.
Chapera, this is yours to take
back with you.
Chapera enjoyed getting clean...
>> I could do this all
day long every day.
>> PROBST: ...as well as getting
the long-awaited rice from their
lock box.
>> Ah! We got rice!
>> For to us have rice in
our system is just like gas in
the tank, and I think it's gonna
give us a little bit, just that
little more... hoochy.
>> PROBST: The rice helped fuel
Chapera to a large lead in a
jolting immunity challenge.
>> Please don't move!
>> Colby, Colby, Colby, Colby.
>> PROBST: Ethan throws it on
Colby.
>> Ow!
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Chapera has their
last piece.
Take your blindfolds off.
Start building the puzzle.
But the pieces didn't fall into
place for Chapera, and Saboga
and Mogo Mogo out-stacked them,
winning shared immunity.
>> ( yelling )
>> PROBST: Facing Tribal
Council, Rob Cesternino looked
for an ally in Boston Rob.
>> I know you know how
to play the game and I know you
know a lot, and I know you would
be very, like, helpful and we
can make good allies.
>> I... I agree.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Rob Cesternino got blindsided by
Boston Rob, and he was the first
person voted out of the Chapera
tribe.
Rob, the tribe has spoken.
>> I was targeted early
for coming close to winning last
time.
It is especially painful to not
have a fair crack at that
million dollars this time
around.
Being as big of a fan
of Survivor as I am and then
having the opportunity not only
to play the game, but to come
back and play an all-star
version of the game was really
the ultimate thrill.
>> PROBST: On Day 13, the tribes
arrived for the reward
challenge, and they were hit
with the first big twist of the
game.
The tribe that finishes last
will be dissolved.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Gonna have a
schoolyard game of pick 'em.
>> That's wild.
>> PROBST: We will alternate
picks.
The winning tribe gets to pick
first.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go Mogo Mogo.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo paddled to
an easy first-place finish.
>> ( cheering )
>> PROBST: Chapera's second-
place finish meant Saboga was
no more.
>> We get to pick first.
>> Okay.
>> We got to get rid of
Ethan.
>> Yup. Yeah.
>> Bring him along, Rich.
>> PROBST: In a strategic move,
Mogo Mogo took Ethan and brought
Jerri along for the ride.
And Chapera took Rupert and
Jenna.
At Chapera, Rupert and Jenna
were immediately impressed by
their new surroundings.
>> Oh...
>> We're home!
We're home.
>> PROBST: And the girls soon
made sure the tribe was united.
>> Jenna, Amber and
myself made necklaces.
We found all the shells and we
bonded them together, and they
quickly became symbolic of the
unity that Chapera has, even
though we have two new members.
We have a present for you.
>> Ah, ha-ha...
>> Now we're all...
>> Cool.
>> I love it.
>> It's kinda cool,
right?
We made necklaces for everybody.
>> Thank you.
>> Oh, I like the way you
guys did these with the wire.
>> Don't they look cool?
This is about Tribal...
>> ALICIA and SUE: Unity.
>> You know, it wasn't
apparent over at Saboga how
close Chapera was.
We knew that they had some sort
of bond that kept them winning
uh... because, you know, they
weren't the biggest, they
weren't the strongest, but they
kept winning the challenges, but
now that I'm over here, I see
that there's really a sense of
tribehood here.
>> I will definitely keep
my necklace on and I hope
everybody else will, too.
I don't think we should be
intimidated by them knowing
that we're a strong tribe and
sticking together.
We're gonna take them down one
by one.
>> PROBST: The competition
heated up on Day 15 when the two
newly formed tribes went-head
to-head at the immunity
challenge.
First one to hit the water is
out.
Boston Rob took control of the
game and led his tribe to
victory.
Chapera wins immunity!
>> You did it! You did
it!
>> PROBST: Back at camp, Colby
changed Mogo Mogo's game plan
when he targeted Richard instead
of Ethan.
>> Richard's the one we
gotta get rid of.
He's the snake in the grass
that's going to cause us the
most trouble.
>> PROBST: But Richard got wind
of the plot when Jerri tipped
him off, putting Colby on thin
ice.
>> Now, Jerri says
she's been approached to get
rid of me.
The only way that could possibly
have happened is Ethan, Lex and
Colby.
Okay. That's it, then, 'cause if
you're not for anything else,
then we'll just do that.
All right, Colby goes.
So they blew it.
How dare you approach somebody
to get rid of me?
You must go bye-bye now.
>> PROBST: Despite the scramble
before Tribal Council, Richard,
the first Survivor winner ever,
was dethroned.
>> I've been
bamboozled!
Man, oh, man.
>> PROBST: Rich, the tribe has
spoken.
>> Food, food.
I hope there's some real
underlying, intelligent,
sophisticated game-playing going
on that undermined me and that
I'm not aware of.
I'd love it more than anything.
I'd be shocked as hell, but it
would be fun to see.
>> PROBST: All right.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> Please.
>> PROBST: Hopefully you'll like
it.
>> ( shrieks )
>> Shish kebabs.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe keeps everything
in the basket.
>> Oh, we gotta win.
>> PROBST: For reward!
Survivors ready! Go!
Mogo Mogo stomped their way to
an early lead...
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: ...and never looked
back.
And with that, Mogo Mogo wins
reward!
>> ( cheering )
>> PROBST: Take these...
and the main course, shish
kebab.
>> Oh, my God, that
smells so good.
>> PROBST: That night, despite
their hard knocks, Chapera vowed
to stay true to each other.
>> Look, guys, we should
be able to win this, if you
think about it, all right?
We're six-strong, they're
six-strong.
And then we can just roll.
>> Let's all make a pact to
stick together.
>> One, two, three, Chapera!
>> PROBST: the next morning,
Mogo Mogo continued to reap the
benefits of their reward.
>> We all decided to dip
into our coffee bean supply to
make some cowboy coffee.
Coffee and sugar.
Oh, it's so delicious.
We all sat down and drank
probably about four cups of the
strongest coffee you can
imagine.
And none of us have had coffee
in about a month.
>> I'm starting to get spun.
>> Oh, but it feels good.
>> It feels so good to
be wired.
>> No more water.
Only coffee.
>> Before we sat down to
the coffee, playing checkers
just wore me out.
At this point I'm ready to draw
a finish line and set up a
100 yard dash and start racing.
>> Suddenly we're a much
more exciting group.
>> Oh, my God, he's going
to do a cartwheel!
>> Yay, coffee!
>> Anybody got some
coffee?
Man, that coffee is good!
>> You drank coffee?
>> I think I had some
coffee.
We had the best coffee of our
entire life.
Who would have thought just
bringing and introducing a
little coffee into the tribe
would have made the biggest
difference in the world?
>> I mean, listen to us,
we're like bamboozled.
This is nuts.
The caffeine is just like
rifling through our bodies.
My eyes are opened.
I mean, I thought I was having
vision problems.
I was also getting my glasses.
I just need caffeine.
Ready.
>> It's a very happy
beach right now.
Don't know how long it will last
but as long as we've got coffee,
we're going to be up and
smiling.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: on day 19, Boston Rob
had his hands full.
>> I'm out here on a
deserted island in Panama, and I
got two beautiful women, and
they want to make a sandwich out
of me.
What am I going to do?
Would you say no?
Seriously, smarten up.
>> Boston Rob and
Amber are very close, and I'm
friends with both of them, so
all three of us sleep connected.
I mean, we're rolling around
hugging each other.
I mean, it's friends.
>> I'm definitely
conscious of Jenna hanging out
with Rob a lot.
And I think it's definitely a
good thing.
It takes some of the tension off
of me and Rob hanging out
together.
I'm not going to get jealous of
any of her hanging on him or
doing anything like that.
I have Boston Rob wrapped around
my little finger.
>> Awesome.
A strategy to everything, you
know?
Like there's strategy to putting
my arm around Jenna while I have
it around Amber at the same
time.
You've got to keep your friends
close, but you got to keep your
enemies closer.
Make no mistake.
I'm here to play Survivor.
At the end of this, hopefully
Amber and I can be having some
fun together, and we'll be
spending my million.
Worst case scenario, we'll be
spending hers.
>> PROBST: At the challenge on
day 19, the tribes learned just
how much was at stake.
In addition to being a reward
challenge, it is also an
immunity challenge.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: One more twist: the
winning tribe will select one
member from the losing tribe to
join them on the reward, which
means they partake in the
barbecue and they avoid Tribal
Council.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Once the challenge got under
way...
Mogo Mogo with a bit of a lead.
Ethan is off heading into the
jungle.
Boston Rob close behind!
>> Come on, Rob!
>> PROBST: ...the race to the
finish line was tight.
We're neck and neck!
In a hard-fought duel, Chapera
pulled out a last-moment
victory.
Mogo Mogo off course now.
Chapera heading straight for
their dock!
Chapera wins reward and
immunity!
( cheers )
Chapera chose to kidnap Kathy.
Kathy.
At first, Kathy wasn't
comfortable leaving her tribe
behind for a day of luxury.
Chapera, by the way, that's your
ride, a 94-foot luxury yacht.
( screams )
But after a barbecue...
>> Some people grabbed
plates.
I didn't even grab a plate.
>> PROBST: ...some dessert...
>> Oh, look at this,
custard.
>> PROBST: ...and a dip under a
tropical waterfall...
( screaming )
Kathy warmed up to her new
friends.
>> I feel totally
welcomed by Chapera.
I mean, they brought me in like
I was one of their tribe
members.
>> ♪ We got a new girl, her name
is Kat ♪
>> We got a new girl, her name
is Kat
>> ♪ She fits in just like that
>> She fits in just like that. ♪
>> PROBST: While Chapera was
cruising, Mogo Mogo was getting
down and dirty.
>> PROBST: but Lex had a
different plan in mind.
>> You don't get far in
this game by playing safe.
I find myself now at the doorway
of an opportunity to do
just that for the first time in
the game, to really do something
that probably no one is going
to expect me to do.
Their plan is to get rid of you
tonight.
>> I knew that was
coming.
>> They think I'm in with
them and that Shii Ann is as
well.
We're going to do Colby tonight.
>> I'm very content with
that decision.
Colby doesn't see this coming at
all.
He doesn't see a single vote
coming in his direction.
And if it took losing today to
get him out of here, I'm totally
fine with it.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Jerri won the game of cat and
mouse and her revenge was
complete.
Colby was the next person voted
out of Survivor All-Stars.
Colby, the tribe has spoken.
>> I had to make
decisions and getting rid of
Richard was a move that my
entire tribe had to make, but I
was left to orchestrate it and
that really just threw me out in
the open.
In the other tribe members eyes,
it seemed as though I was trying
to become the power player, the
shape-shifter.
It wasn't that at all, but
unfortunately that's the way the
game goes.
>> PROBST: on day 20 with Colby
gone, Ethan realized he was
still treading water.
>> I thought everything
was going smoothly and, boom, I
thought I was pretty close to
Lex.
Not anymore.
I don't know what I'm going to
do here.
>> PROBST: Later that day, the
tribes played for a chance to
loot items from the other camp.
Here we go.
First match-up, start spinning.
Chapera's balancing act led them
to a win.
>> Run, run, run!
Run, run, run!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: And Jenna was sent to
Mogo Mogo to retrieve a grill, a
bag of rice, and a Hawaiian
sling.
>> I've been waiting 20
days to not have to poke fish
with a stick.
I'm going to be the hunter
tomorrow.
>> PROBST: while Rupert
salivaged over the sling, Boston
Rob and Amber's relationship
reached new heights.
>> You're not ever
supposed to feel secure in this
game, but with Rob and I having
an alliance, I feel 99.9%
secure.
>> PROBST: The following morning
a fishing competition began to
brew between Boston Rob and
Rupert.
>> Rupert is all excited
about having the Hawaiian sling.
You know, it's his baby.
Now he can catch a fish and show
how much he's worth to the
tribe.
First of all, the guy looks like
Grizzly Adams but he thinks he
Aquaman in the ocean.
And he comes back with a bag of
fish feeling all good about
himself.
>> My God, it took all I
had to stop.
>> I proceeded to go
into the water and catch 11 fish
myself.
Boston-style.
>> Sometimes I really
like Boston Rob.
>> I got two at one time
on one of them.
>> Other times I see
kind of an arrogant pain in the
ass.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, it was a dismal show
of marksmanship.
Before Chapera narrowly escaped
with victory.
Chapera wins immunity!
Mogo Mogo heading to Tribal
Council.
Back at Mogo Mogo, Lex took his
old friend Ethan aside and gave
him some bad news.
>> I think it's just better
for my game if we vote you out
tonight.
It has nothing to do with
friendship.
This is business.
I've got my own agenda this
time.
I've got my own plan.
It doesn't include him.
This isn't Africa.
This is All-Star.
>> PROBST: But Ethan wasn't
about to go down without a
fight.
He approached Kathy with a plan.
>> There's no rhyme or
reason of how Lex is playing
this game.
There will be no sense of
security with Lex at any time.
>> But I don't want to
take Lex out before Jerri.
>> No.
>> It will be Jerri
tonight, all right.
>> So I'll vote for Jerri
and then you and Shii Ann can
talk about it.
And I'm a gambler.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Ethan's gamble didn't pay off.
He was the next person voted out
of Survivor All-Stars.
Ethan, the tribe has spoken.
>> I've been just
struggling since day one trying
to fight and bite and scramble
my way through this game.
And I lasted 21 days.
And I'm proud.
I made it further than any other
winner.
I have the title of Survivor:
Africa champion, and no one can
take that away from me.
No matter what I do from this
point on for the rest of my
life, I have that, and that's a
good feeling.
>> PROBST: Where once 18
all-stars stood, now only ten
remain.
What experiences and twists
await Big Tom, Amber, Boston
Rob, Alicia, Rupert, Jenna, Lex,
Kathy, Jerri and Shii Ann as
they attempt to outlast all the
others and become the ultimate
sole Survivor?
Join us next week as the
adventure continues.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
Being on a losing team all the
time is just depressing.
The gap between both the tribes
couldn't be wider.
>> We were just tickled today.
>> But while everyone is talking
merge-
>> I'm ready for merge, I'm
ready for all this to be one
tribe.
What happens next will turn
their world upside down.
Drop your buffs.
I feel like I'm one who got
screwed in this whole situation.
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Just another beautiful day here
on the island.
Of Shapire isnt it?
Little overcast.
Little overcast, Silas.
Wind breezing in your face.
Out of the northwest.
Just smell that?
(deep inhale)
(deep exhales)
You need another shower bro.
(chuckles)