>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: At the reward
challenge, the tribes faced the
first big twist of the game.
The losing tribe will not return
back to your beach.
The tribe members will be
absorbed by the two remaining
tribes.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: The tribes battled to
keep themselves together, but it
was Mogo Mogo who cruised to an
easy first place finish.
Mogo Mogo wins reward.
Giving them first pick from the
losing Saboga tribe.
In a strategic move, Mogo Mogo
picked Ethan and brought Jerri
along for the ride.
>> The biggest reward was
dismantling Saboga.
>> PROBST: And Chapera chose
Rupert and Jenna.
>> Welcome aboard.
>> PROBST: At Chapera, Rupert
and Jenna were happy to have a
new home.
>> Our camp was Hobo Junction.
Theirs is the Taj Mahal.
>> PROBST: Things got physical
when the two tribes battled for
immunity.
>> Come on, Sue, you got it.
>> Sue, get up there.
>> I want this one.
Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: And Sue had a close
encounter with Richard.
Guys, come on.
As Boston Rob led the new
Chapera tribe to victory.
Before Tribal Council, the
scramble was on when Colby
suddenly changed the plan to
vote out Ethan.
>> Richard's the one we've
we've got to get rid of.
He's a cancer in this tribe.
>> PROBST: When Richard found
out, he teamed up with the girls
to foil Colby's plan.
>> How dare you approach
somebody to get rid of me?
You must go bye-bye now.
>> PROBST: And Kathy found
herself caught in the middle.
>> Give me ten minutes.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Colby spoke out.
>> You cannot coast, although
a lot of people are doing it.
>> PROBST: And proved he was a
power to be reckoned with when
his plan succeeded.
The fifth person voted out of
Survivor: All-Stars, Rich.
>> I've been bamboozled.
>> PROBST: The first Survivor
winner, Richard Hatch, was voted
out.
>> Food, food...
>> PROBST: 15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> Last night was the
biggest scramble at the last
minute as Richard Hatch was
scurrying about trying to save
his own butt.
Right as we were leaving for
Tribal Council, we grabbed our
torches and I looked at Kathy
and I said, "Who are we voting
for?"
And she said "Hatch."
>> I have some
questions for you Kath.
>> Yes, darling.
>> What happened last night?
>> Yeah.
>> The decision last
night at Tribal for me was I
could have swung Shii Ann and
Jerri to vote for Colby.
Instead, I decided to stay with
what Colby wanted, which was to
vote Richard Hatch off.
>> He's the Richard Hatch
now of the group.
>> Don't give me that
loyalty ..., Colby.
I tried to put together my gut
instincts about what it was
going to be like to come back to
the tribe,
having made that big decision to
oust Colby without consulting
with Lex.
I just think the repercussion
would put a schism between
myself and Lex, and Lex would
feel totally betrayed.
And I know Lex.
He then would never trust me, so
in the 11th hour, I decided to
vote for Richard Hatch.
I saved Colby's ass.
I made it look like we saved
him.
>> You're so powerful right now.
Kathy's the biggest power player
of all.
She's got all of us wrapped
around her fingers.
And if nobody's noticing that,
she's one darn good player.
>> That's where you put the
strap in?
>> Uh-huh.
See, and it's such a good spear
it's already drawn blood on me,
so I know it's going to draw
blood on fish.
>> That's good.
>> Hell, yeah.
I love that.
>> To be honest with you,
it put pressure on me when
Rupert and Jenna come because it
threw another cog in the game,
but I really like old Rupert.
He's kind of like me, he's easy-
going, nothing don't bother him.
And I know it may cost me down
the road because, you know, he
could easily take my place.
I wonder if down here in this
little cove right here, it'll be
shallower.
>> The role of provider
is wide open here.
I like the fact that none of
them could fish.
>> Rupert?
>> Yeah?
>> You want them both?
>> Ah, good.
A few of them would eat the
snails, that attach to the sides
of the rock, but I want to be
the guy that brings, you know,
a couple of dozen oysters and a
couple fish in every day.
>> You want help picking
those up?
>> No. I'm doing all right, man.
We're never going to take them
all anyway.
You always got to leave some
back so the other guys know
where to come.
>> Sue is playing her own game.
>> ( humming tune )
>> She wants to be that
provider, but the only meat that
she's providing right now are
those cone snails, which I think
most of the people eat.
>> First, nobody likes
these damn things.
Now everybody likes them.
It sort of pisses me off because
I'm not eating the rice.
Oh, recollect.
>> I want to catch some fish.
Grizzly Adams out there trying
to pretend like he's a big man.
He brought home two little fish
the whole time he's been here.
Rupert's catching fish-- I'm
happy.
He can continue to feed me until
it's time for him to go, and
that time will be determined by
me.
So he'd better catch a lot of
fish, keep my belly full.
>> My strategy of
flying under the radar was
pointed out by Colby last night,
which by the way, was not the
smartest move on his part, to
say, "Well, those who are flying
under the radar are not going to
get by me."
I felt like that was a direct
attack at me.
>> Shii Ann, you've said
before, you know, you guys just
tell me what we're doing and I'm
good with that.
I didn't have any respect for
that game plan the first time I
played this game.
It's just very easy to allow
someone else to be the bad guy.
And yesterday, that was me.
>> You think you were
the bad guy yesterday?
>> Ultimately I ended up
almost getting chopped because I
sat up on that hill and told
Ethan he had nothing to worry
about, that we were going for
Richard.
And then I came down and lied
right to Richard's face and told
him the same thing.
Someone like you doesn't have to
lie this entire game because you
don't make a decision.
It's very easy to sit in a tent,
wait until an hour before Tribal
Council for someone to walk in
and tell you who we're voting
for and say, "Okay, I'll go
along with that."
Man, that's an easy game to
play.
That's an easy game to make it a
long way.
I don't have had any respect for
that.
If that's your game, that's a
very brilliant game.
It will work, but you can't...
>> Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Lecture, lecture, lecture.
Captain America with his good
teeth, nice smile, handsome guy.
I'm just like... ( snoring ).
Oh, I'm sorry. Are you done?
>> Everyone's got to play...
>> I agree.
>> ...and it takes more
than just showing up and writing
a name on a ticket to be a
player in this game, as far as
I'm concerned.
>> He doesn't respect
my game-- I don't necessarily
respect his.
We're equal.
But I'm not dumb enough to tell
him that.
>> Which one looks like a
lucky coconut?
This one.
>> Can you imagine us going into
a merge seven to four?
>> That'd be great.
>> Even seven to five.
I'd be thrilled.
It guarantees us all seven at
least.
>> We're kind of sitting
back and watching what's going
on and waiting to go see what
happens.
We don't really know Jenna and
Rupert all that well.
We haven't played with them.
They just came into this tribe a
few days ago.
Now we won the first immunity
challenge against Mogo Mogo
since we've formed seven in each
tribe.
Be interesting to see who they
vote off.
>> Yeah. Hell, yeah.
>> The next thing that we want
to see is who gets voted out.
They had to go to Tribal
Council.
Who'd they vote out?
>> I think Jerri's gone.
>> They may be tired of old
Hatch.
I would be.
>> I wish.
>> Richard probably is
making them insane.
I would do my damnedest to have
him voted off the first time we
lost.
>> Oh, I hope they vote him
off, you guys.
If Ethan's getting fish, I hope
to God they vote him off.
I still can't... they better
talk to Richard about what he
did to me at that challenge.
>> That was tough.
>> Anything that Richard
could have done...
was, like, what he does, he does
all the time-- he just gets
naked.
Well, at this point, we're over
it.
So yesterday, what happened at
the challenge, he throws his
hands up in the air and thrusts
his hips and starts rubbing
himself on me.
He does not deserve to be here.
Anybody that's won, as far as
I'm concerned, Ethan and, like,
Rich should be the first ones to
go.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, I will go hug them all.
>> Nights are really long here.
They're like 12 hours long. It's
awful.
All night I laid there thinking
every time I woke up, I could
re-feel Richard naked.
It kept flashing through my
head.
And I started feeling really
bad.
Like why did he have to touch
me?
He didn't touch nobody else.
Why didn't he just walk by me?
>> You know why, 'cause
the more she thinks about it,
she's like, "My husband's going
to know about this."
He's going to freak out.
I mean it's not a good scenario
for her.
>> She probably wants to
be alone right now, huh?
>> This morning when we
woke up, Sue was not herself.
I didn't realize how much she
had been affected by what
happened to her until she
started to cry.
It's affecting us because it's
affecting you, but we're all
right.
I mean, we're more worried about
you than anything, do you know
what I mean?
>> I mean, it's, like, gross.
I've been with one partner for
20 years.
Never even thought about kissing
another guy.
>> There was nothing you
could do, Sue.
You know he's not going to be
mad at you.
>> There's something I can
do and I ain't going to get it
done laying on this beach.
>> You need to get it
all out, Sue.
Just be mad, be upset.
She just couldn't control her
tears, and she couldn't control
her anger.
It's really hard to try to
console somebody who feels that
way.
There was nothing I can do.
>> I think sleeping on
it, she must have thought about
it all night last night.
>> Yeah, she did.
She's thinking about her husband
and she's really upset about it.
>> It's like another one of
those situations, Amber, where,
like, you don't know... is she
just ... around because like,
she's a smart player and she's
trying to get some money out of
this, she wants to sue him or
is like, just something that's
really bothering her?
But a situation this serious,
you can't even screw around.
You got to give her the benefit
of the doubt.
Sue is either, A) Looking to
cash in on a huge payday-- sue
the ... out of Richard Hatch;
Or Sue is really emotionally
distraught by the whole thing.
Or Sue's using this as some kind
of a leverage to play the game
of Survivor.
Nobody knows what Sue's thinking
except Sue.
>> I think it's just
gotten worse and worse in her
head as it's gone along.
I think maybe at first she was
thinking, oh, you know, I can
get him for this.
But now it's really starting to
bother her.
As the day went on, she had more
and more time to think about it.
And when you're out here playing
this game, your mind does crazy
things.
And so I think that just made
the situation worse.
I think if we were in another
situation not even playing
Survivor and that would have
happened, it might not have been
as big as a deal maybe as it
turned out to be.
>> You hungry, Sue?
You want to cook those eyeballs
up?
>> No.
>> You holler when you
want to cook them-- we'll cook
them up and fry them up.
Sue was distant, nonresponsive,
throwing in the towel.
Are you okay?
At the time of the challenge and
all the contact and all that
with Richard, Sue could have
handled it different.
She could have stopped right
then and said "foul."
Instead, she turns her head,
says, "Oh, that's gross," and
goes on.
Thinks about it, processes it,
comes up with her own agenda,
and goes on with that.
>> You can't argue her point.
I don't feel what she's feeling.
I don't.
I mean, it didn't happen to me.
I couldn't possibly understand
how... She's humiliated.
She feels completely humiliated.
>> That's right.
>> Earlier, Sue was vital
to this tribe that we couldn't
get rid of her.
But I want it to be known right
up, by God, I don't need her.
She's very overbearing, and in
my opinion, if it was up to old
jungle cat, I say stick a fork
in her, she's done.
>> What I'm doing is I'm
making a grocery list.
It's ending up being pretty much
all sweet, but I've got... I
started off pretty healthy.
Coming from Saboga, we really
had a food advantage on our
island.
We had an endless supply of
plantains, tons of coconuts.
And then I get here to Mogo Mogo
and all they have right now is
rice.
I need honey-roasted extra
crunchy peanut butter, Peanut
Butter Crunch, marshmallows, big
and small.
Bananas, apples... gala apples.
>> I hate talking about
food this early in the game.
It drives me crazy because then
all after sudden I have this
mirage in my brain, you know, of
just this big giant ice cream
sundae.
It doesn't make me feel good to
get cravings.
>> Milk chocolate chips, peanut
butter chips, marshmallow creme,
graham crackers with cinnamon...
>> I am a little bit
concerned about the food
situation.
I don't like the fact that our
main food provider got voted out
because I knew every day he'd
bring back a fish.
Oh, Richard Hatch, I miss you
already.
Where is the fish?
>> I actually thought
about that this morning.
I thought about getting up
and going out with a sling.
>> You haven't tried it
yet, have you?
>> Not here, no.
I want to.
I really wanted to wait until
Richard was out of the picture
before I picked up the spear
because I didn't want it to be
a competitive thing.
I knew that Richard was really
kind of territorial with the
whole fishing chore, and that
was fine.
>> Good luck.
>> Easy.
>> Yes!
>> He's a natural.
>> I wanted to take on
the fisherman's role.
However, I didn't try to fish
today.
I'm sitting back a little bit,
you know, I let him do it all
today.
>> Sharp shooter.
We should have gotten rid of
Richard a long time ago.
>> I didn't think it was
necessary to let everyone know
that I was an accomplished
fisherman.
I think kind of holding your
cards a little closer is always
a good idea in Survivor.
>> Yay, the heroes.
It's so funny.
You guys look like the guys have
been out for days getting food.
>> I got three or four
different kinds.
There's some small ones for
flavor.
>> Oh, my God, Lex!
They're awesome.
Look at them all laid out.
It's like a trophy room.
>> Wow.
Lex is a competitor.
This is not his first rodeo, as
we say in Texas.
Because of his ability to fish,
that is something you check in
the back of your mind knowing
that ultimately I'm competing
against Lex. Wow.
>> What a treat, getting
a taste of all these different
kinds of fish.
>> I know.
It's fun.
>> I think that I've got the
favor of the girls right now.
If I can show them that I can
provide them with food, there's
no reason for them to feel any
compulsion to keep the other two
guys around.
>> I came in yesterday, felt
like a sacrificial lamb.
>> Right.
>> Like, just, I felt
Rupert can get you guys food and
stuff, but, like, if you guys
are serious...
>> No, we're dead serious
because me and Rob want to save
our asses.
Like, I'm trying to save my ass
but I know Sue wants to get
rid of me.
Rob and I came up with the idea
to approach Rupert and Jenna,
tell them that you know, we
think we're on the outs, we
think we're in trouble.
We'll save you if you save us.
>> But what makes us
believe that you guys aren't
coming to us like Alicia came to
you?
>> What would we have to
lose by coming to you, you know?
>> I don't know.
>> Momentum is huge in
this game.
When you have it, you want to
keep it.
Rupert has a squeaky clean image
and attitude.
There's something about him I
just don't trust, so I, uh,
I formed an alliance with him.
>> We are taking a huge
risk at you guys going back and
telling the other guys.
>> No, trust me.
I'd much rather go in with you
guys.
>> But I just, and I felt that
you guys would hopefully
want to go with us.
>> Yes.
No, we do.
>> Hell, yes.
>> When I first
started this Survivor: All-
Star and I hear people
talking and you know saying
that they want to help me, or
saying that they want me on
their side, I couldn't trust any
of them.
Now after 16 days, I know that
I can trust Jenna, I hope that
I can trust Rob and Amber.
I feel pretty confident with
where I'm at.
>> If you honestly
honor your alliance, you go to
the end, no matter what.
But always somebody, like,
gets greedy at one point.
Once it gets to the final
four, then we can, you know,
every man for themselves.
>> Exactly.
>> You got to look at me.
>> I'm cool with it if
you guys are cool with it.
You have my word.
>> I'm beautiful with it.
>> All right, done.
I've got alliances with
everybody now, except Sue and
Alicia.
I mean, we can turn around
tomorrow and kick Jenna and
Rupert off.
They can be here as
sacrificial lambs.
We've got to see what's going
on.
It's my game, buddy.
>> Why do we have tree mail?
>> "You'll do some high-
stepping while rewards sail
through the sky, so wave your
hands and stomp your feet.
Your taste buds will tell you
why."
This is coffee in here, by the
way.
( sniffing )
Smell.
>> Oh, my God.
>> We could try to make
coffee with this.
>> Oh, my God, I'd be
up for five days.
I've been dying all day today
to be alone with Lex for a few
minutes, just to kind of put
things in order.
Listen, Lex, I just want you
to know, you can trust me.
>> Okay.
>> 150,000%.
>> I absolutely adore you.
>> Okay.
And you know I trust you, too.
>> Good.
And I want you to.
>> I do.
>> Because I, personally,
out of everybody here,
would love to go with you.
>> I appreciate that, Jerri.
The conversation I had with
Jerri was completely sincere.
I don't have any reason to
feel that it was anything but.
But I am going to do whatever
it takes to get me further in
the game, and that if that
means exploiting situations
where I have a friend that
might trust me, I'll do it.
It's business this time.
>> What if the reward
challenge was a grill and
seasonings and some meat...
>> Some seasonings?
>> Oh, my god.
>> And a bottle of wine.
>> Two bottles of wine.
>> Five bottles.
>> Five bottles of wine.
>> That'd be the best
reward right now.
>> Every day, we talk
about food out here because as
good as the rice is, it's
terrible.
And it has there has to be
some light at the end of the
tunnel.
We're starving over here.
>> Are you hungry, Sue?
>> No.
>> That's coming from
a guy who's been fighting with
her from day one.
>> Yeah, it is.
I hate it.
>> Sue is Sue.
She will endure and pursue her
own agenda.
She doesn't give a damn about
what anybody else is doing.
Ultimately, Sue having her own
agenda, will hinder her.
It alienates her from the
tribe.
>> How do we make it back
again?
>> We are going to win.
>> We win and we eat.
>> We're going to win.
>> We support her
100%, but we're also thinking
this puts us in a bad place as
a tribe.
We still have to play this
game.
>> PROBST: Come on in, Chapera.
Mogo Mogo, come on in.
You're getting your first look
at the new Mogo Mogo tribe.
Richard Hatch voted out at
last night's Tribal Council.
>> Good move.
>> PROBST: Before we get to
today's challenge, I want to
address something that
happened yesterday.
Richard Hatch, sort of being
inappropriate...
>> Sort of, yeah.
>> PROBST: Anybody have any
comments?
>> I was sexually violated.
To have some guy come up...
He passed a half dozen people
on platforms and never touched
them.
>> PROBST: Sue, I'm...
>> And it went too far
and he crossed the line, and
he crossed the line with me.
>> PROBST: Well...
>> SUE: Okay, I know you don't
know, and you didn't see it
because his back was to you
and he's too big of a ... slob
to see around.
I was violated, humiliated,
dehumanized and totally spent,
Jeff.
It wasn't "sort of," Jeff
'cause his back was to you,
Jeff.
That's all I'm saying and I'm
... spent and I'm done with
this ... game.
There's no way I can continue
with my ... emotions pushed to
the ground that much.
>> PROBST: So...
Okay, so you're... when you
say you're done with the game,
as in you want out of the
game?
>> I'm done.
I'm walking away.
>> PROBST: Let me ask you guys,
did anything come up at your
camp about it?
>> No, we... I...
>> I didn't know what happened.
>> PROBST: You didn't see it?
>> We didn't even notice.
>> It was all done in
front of our platform.
>> Yeah, I saw it, Sue.
And the thing is, trust me,
you know from the first
season, maybe you guys don't,
living with a guy being naked
sucks 'cause he's naked all
the time.
>> I didn't give a ... if
he was naked, if he had just
walked by me and never ...
touched me, I'd have been
fine, but he didn't, that's
the ... point.
>> PROBST: Does it have any
impact that he's out of the
game or not?
>> No, I-I...
No, my mind's ... left this
game 24 hours ago.
>> PROBST: Let's, uh... if we
can, bring in this boat, ASAP.
>> I'm so sorry, Sue.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't see him...
>> You guys, good luck.
>> We love you.
( indistinct talking )
( engine puttering )
>> Boy, is that discouraging.
>> PROBST: Okay.
I'll tell you what I suggest,
you tell me what you want to
do.
Here are the two options--
we continue, we play the
reward, winner takes all, just
like always.
Or we forego the reward, you
guys can sit down here and
talk about it and we'll split
this up, you can take it back
to camp with you and eat on
your own.
You tell me what you want to
do.
>> Let's go.
>> Maybe we should sit
down and all share the food
and fix animosity between two
tribes, instead of playing.
>> No, let's play.
We're here to play.
>> I say we play it.
>> We want to play.
>> It's been a long night,
long day.
>> Let's get back to some
normalcy.
>> Let's have some fun.
>> PROBST: So the decision is...
>> We're going to play.
>> PROBST: Play on.
All right, it's been an odd 16
days...
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: ...but let's get to
today's reward challenge.
Fortunately, it's fun, it's
reward, it's for food.
Here's how it's going to work.
You're going to be stomping
items into a basket eight feet
in the air.
Each tribe will have a basket.
Underneath the basket is an
adjustable plank.
One tribe member at a time,
you'll put one food item on
one end of the plank, you'll
stomp on it.
That'll catapult it into the
air and hopefully into the
basket.
Each tribe member is
responsible for one item going
in that basket.
You can't move on until that
person has achieved that goal.
Here are the six items--
there's sugar, pineapple,
mixed nuts, coffee, oranges,
and beef.
First tribe to get all six
items in their basket wins
reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> Yeah, please.
>> Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
>> PROBST: Hopefully you'll like
it.
( cheering )
>> Shish kabob!
>> Meat.
>> PROBST: They're very nice.
You got some filet mignon, you
got some peppers.
You have some mushrooms and
some red onion and also some
utensils.
In addition, the winning tribe
keeps everything in the
basket.
>> Oh, yes.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Oh, we've got to win.
>> That's it.
>> PROBST: We're even up six,
six, that means everybody
competes.
Get your order, wait for my
go.
( cheering )
>> Mogo Mogo!
>> Here we go, Tommy, here we
go!
>> PROBST: For reward, survivors
ready?
Go!
( cheering )
>> Yeah, Ethan.
You got it, baby.
>> PROBST: Ethan and Big Tom.
Allies from Africa.
Ooh, Ethan just overshoots it.
Big Tom is in on his first
toss.
( Tom shouts indistinctly )
>> Yeah, good job.
>> PROBST: Ethan's in on his
second.
We're tied up 1-1.
Jenna and Shii Ann.
>> Turn your board over, Shii
Ann.
>> Come on, Jenna.
>> Make sure it's in a groove.
Shii Ann.... oh!
So close.
( indistinct shouting )
>> Move forward, Jenna.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann hits for
Mogo Mogo.
Mogo Mogo 2, Chapera 1.
Jenna still just missing to
the right.
Jerri... oh!
In and out. Lips it.
>> Line the board that way!
>> PROBST: Jenna getting a
little help from her tribe
mates-- adjust the aim.
>> You're all right, Jerri.
>> PROBST: That's three for Mogo
Mogo.
Wait till she gets back.
>> Forget the hat!
Colby up for Mogo Mogo.
Mogo Mogo 3, Chapera one.
Shish kabob at stake.
Jenna... no.
>> Jenna, way over.
All the way over.
>> Nice and straight, Jenna.
>> You got it.
>> That's it, go!
>> Move the board!
Move the board!
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Just... And Mogo
Mogo's in with four items.
( cheering )
>> Come on, Jenna.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
>> ... it.
>> Here we go, here we go.
Game on.
>> PROBST: Jenna hits it for
Chapera with the one-legged
stomp.
>> ...
>> PROBST: Boston Rob trying to
make up some time.
>> There you go.
Don't worry about it.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo with four,
Chapera with two.
>> Go, Kathy.
>> You got it, Kathy.
You got it.
You got it, Kathy.
>> PROBST: Kathy...
just misses for Mogo Mogo.
>> Come on, Rob.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob nails it
for Chapera.
Kathy nails it for Mogo Mogo.
We're at five, three.
Go, go.
Lex with the last item for Mogo
Mogo.
If he gets the beef in, it's
reward for Mogo Mogo.
>> Come on, Alicia!
>> PROBST: Alicia trying to
catch up for Chapera.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: One toss...
just over.
Alicia hits it on her first
shot.
>> Come on, Alicia.
>> PROBST: Chapera with four.
Mogo Mogo with five.
Amber's going to have to make up
a lot of time.
Lex can win it for Mogo Mogo
with this.
( Jerri screaming )
He just misses.
( people shouting )
>> PROBST: And with that, Mogo
Mogo wins reward.
( cheering )
>> Whoo!
>> Good try, Amber.
( cheering and hooting )
>> PROBST: All right, Mogo Mogo,
utensils.
>> Barbecue.
( Shii Ann screaming )
>> PROBST: Take these.
>> Oh!
>> Big smell.
>> PROBST: And the main
course...
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: ...shish kebobs.
Sadly, Chapera, nothing for you.
>> Whatever.
>> PROBST: Been an eventful day?
>> Yeah.
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: Tomorrow's another
day.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: You guys can head
back to camp.
>> Thank you.
( cheering and shouting )
>> Mogo Mogo! Yeah!
( hooting )
>> All I know is tonight
we ain't talking about it.
We're eating it.
>> We're eating it.
>> That's right.
>> We got these seven
kebabs of filet mignon.
We just couldn't wait to put it
on that fire and start grilling
it up.
>> It sounds good.
>> It does.
>> Oh, yeah, baby, look at this.
>> The steak kebabs were
more delectable than...
Excuse me while I clear the
saliva out of my mouth.
>> How is it, Ethan?
Is it cooked enough, buddy?
>> Yeah, I mean I don't
even...
I can't tell you the last time I
had a steak or meat or anything.
>> How come? You don't eat meat?
>> Uh-uh.
>> Yeah, you do today.
>> It was good.
I just wanted to rub my face in
it.
I wanted to sleep next to it.
Oh!
>> To a great win.
>> Mm-hmm.
Hear, hear.
>> Unbelievable team.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yeah.
>> I hope there's no ill will
on the other side because we
didn't take any of the stuff
and share it.
>> They wanted to play.
>> Yeah?
>> Well, that's the
thing, is-is having Sue leave
and then losing the challenge,
they're going back somewhat
demoralized, yeah.
>> No, no, yeah, that's...
Yeah, it's going to hurt them.
>> It's a good thing Rich
wasn't here.
>> Oh.
I don't even want to think about
what that scene would have been.
>> I think he would be
mortified.
I think the guy does have a
soul.
>> I know Richard Hatch.
As jerky as he might seem, he is
not someone who would purposely
go and sexually violate someone.
>> Angry woman.
>> She must have been
feeling something awful for 24
hours to have exploded like
that.
>> Uh.
>> I felt terrible for
her that she felt so violated
and that she felt so humiliated
and insulted.
Very mixed emotions.
>> I thought it was brutal.
I know it's a horrible thing
that happened, but my God.
That was hard for all of us
to hear.
I don't like her for it.
I'm sorry.
I know she went through a lot.
Still, you got to learn how to
contain your emotions.
I was really offended that she'd
bring us that far into her core
of hatred.
I didn't like it.
So...
I don't know if that's
mean-spirited, but that's how I
feel.
>> You think she was
influenced?
You think Sue was influenced...
to do what she did by leaving
the game?
>> You know?
I sat and talked with her for an
hour up here, trying to convince
her that she could still...
She could still pursue whatever
she wanted without throwing the
game away.
You know, now as it stands, we
kind of gave them a hell of a
gift.
>> Yeah.
>> We didn't give them anything.
>> We didn't.
Sue gave them a hell of a gift.
With Richard getting voted off,
Sue walking out, and losing the
challenge, three strikes--
Chapera was almost out for a few
minutes.
>> All right.
>> Look, guys, there's no
reason why, no matter what, we
should be able to win this, if
you think about it, right?
We're six strong, they're six
strong.
And then we can just roll, one
right after another, after
another.
>> If we stay strong together...
>> Then it comes down to us six.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Then whatever.
>> I agree wholehearted.
>> Let's all make a pact
to stick together.
>> You want to do that?
>> Yes.
>> This is it, guys.
( all talking )
>> I'm in it, no matter what.
>> No matter what.
>> Go, Chapera.
>> One, two, three...
>> Chapera!
>> We all promised each
other we'd stick together no
matter what.
What that really means, I don't
know, but it's a good gesture,
and it's a good show of faith.
>> Hmm!
>> Get ready.
>> Rupe, what's the look
on the face?
>> We got tree mail.
>> All right.
>> Oh, let's see.
"A friend of yours has left the
game.
There will be no challenge
played tonight."
>> Heads down.
( humming )
>> Let's have a moment
of silence for Sue.
>> For Sue.
>> So, I need to...
>> Too bad we don't have any
whiskey to show her how we
really feel.
( Rupert laughs )
>> Let's have some rice.
>> Let's drink to her.
>> Is it ready for lunch
already?
>> Let's have a drink.
>> It means a lot to lose
a member of our tribe,
especially the way that we had
to lose Sue.
But you can never count out
Chapera for making a sad moment
into a happy moment.
We're the happy tribe, and
somehow, we always find a way to
laugh about it.
>> I miss her so much.
>> It was a sad day in Bedrock.
>> It was...
It was heart-wrenching.
>> It's hard to get over.
( laughs )
>> I wasn't real happy with...
I mean, I know Big Tom and Sue
didn't get along, but his
insensitivity in doing the
"Sue's Gone" dance,
I think is pretty crummy.
We lost a valuable member of
this tribe.
She was like a guy.
Sue is hard-core.
And we can count on her every
time we went to a challenge.
And everybody knows that.
I don't care if you like her or
you don't like her.
>> Ah, Sue...
>> Well, at least that's what
we assumed.
>> Right.
>> It's somewhat of a relief.
>> Sue is out of the game.
We're going to be six to six.
>> And at least we know that
it's playing out the fair way
we wanted it to.
>> That's right.
>> Yes...
That's the most important.
>> It definitely disappoints me
that Sue couldn't keep it
together.
I mean, I can't help but wish
that she was still here.
We were up a member.
But Survivor's true test is, if
you're able to keep it together
and keep each other happy, then
you're good to go.
Yeah, we've had bad days, we
have our lows, but we have so
many more highs.
And that's what we concentrate
on in this tribe.
We don't even think about our
lows for very long.
We always think about the highs.
>> All right, people, come
forward.
>> My girls.
My girls know how to make rice.
>> That's right.
>> Oh, my God.
>> You can keep the
oysters and the snails.
This is what Survivor is all
about.
( Rupert laughs )
Rice, baby, rice.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>>PROBST: Next time on Survivor:
>> That woman is such a...
>> PROBST: At Mogo Mogo,
the claws come out.
>> I don't want any of the rice.
I don't really care.
>> I say, put the boxing
gloves on.
>> PROBST: And Lex makes some
bold plans for the future.
>> ( whispering ): If we can
pull this off, we're so in
there.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
One more twist.
( all gasping )