>> ( speaking Spanish )
>> JEFF PROBST: We've returned
to the waters of the Pacific
Ocean just off the coast of
Panama for the greatest Survivor
yet.
In order to ensure top secrecy,
we are under full military
escort.
The air space has been shut
down.
The waters have been cleared.
Just below me are three boats,
all out of sight of each other.
Onboard each boat, six people.
These are the Survivor all-
stars, 18 former castaways
returning to play the ultimate
game one more time.
Each survivor has been given one
canteen and very little
information.
Aside from their own tribe
mates, they have no idea who
else is in the game.
They don't even know there are
three tribes.
When they arrive at their
respective beaches, they will
find only one machete, to be
shared by the entire tribe.
And that's it.
No food, no fire, no help.
It's the least amount of
supplies ever given to a group
of survivors.
They say they're the best of
the best.
Well, it's time to prove it.
Have they learned from their
past, or are they doomed to make
the same mistakes again?
And will old relationships come
back to help them or haunt them?
39 days, 18 all-stars, one
survivor.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> PROBST: These 18 all-stars
divided into three tribes are
about to begin the most
competitive Survivor ever.
The Mogo Mogo tribe, which will
always wear green, consists of:
Jenna Morasca, winner of
Survivor: Amazon.
Kathy Vavrick-O'Brien, Survivor:
Marquesas.
Richard Hatch, winner, Survivor:
Borneo.
Colby Donaldson, Survivor: The
Australian Outback.
Lex Van Den Berghe, Survivor:
Africa,
and Shii Ann Huang, Survivor:
Thailand.
The Saboga tribe, which will
always wear yellow, consists of
Rudy Boesch, Survivor: Borneo.
Tina Wesson, winner of Survivor:
The Australian Outback.
Jenna Lewis, Survivor: Borneo.
Ethan Zohn, winner of Survivor:
Africa.
Jerri Manthey, Survivor: The
Australian Outback
and Rupert Boneham, Survivor:
Pearl Islands.
The Chapera Tribe, which will
always wear red, consists of:
Rob Cesternino, Survivor:
Amazon,
Rob Mariano, Survivor:
Marquesas,
Alicia Calaway, Survivor: The
Australian Outback,
Sue Hawk, Survivor: Borneo,
Amber Brkich, Survivor: The
Australian Outback
and Tom Buchanan, Survivor:
Africa.
( whooping )
>> My tribe is a very
eclectic group and it's gonna be
really interesting to watch how
this shakes out.
I can't wait to start wheeling
dealing and building shelters
and winning challenges and vote
people out.
>> You know, it's hard for
me to realize-- I'm 48.
I've got young 'uns their age,
but I'm here for the new race.
This ain't a little boy's game.
It's for the big boys.
>> All-Star Survivor
is gonna be so cut-throat it's
not even gonna be fun.
Nobody trusts anybody. Nobody.
Nobody trusts anybody, you
understand?
>> Well, let's see.
>> Hey, we got a machete anyway.
>> Yeah, we got a note.
>> All right, honey.
>> You ready?
>> Yes.
>> It's a map.
>> It's a map, to the
water and to the burnt log.
>> It's weird, because
we know each other.
You know who to be careful of,
who not to be careful of, who
are friends, who are not
friends.
Like, everybody knows, if you
push my buttons you may get me
to crack, an-and that could be
my demise.
>> Is that way...?
Which way is north?
>> Hey! I-I...
Hey, I think this is it.
We've either found the water or-
or a big john, one.
>> Oh, no.
>> That looks like milk to me.
We have well water, and it's
highly contaminated.
You're gonna get all these
diseases if you don't boil it.
We have no fire.
I mean, it's just like they
dropped you off, all right, go.
Go ahead.
There's a cooking pot and
machete... a water source.
What you would do?
>> Our supplies here are
extremely meager.
As all-star survivors, we don't
have anything to build a fire
with so, I think shelter is the
primary concern.
>> What about this space right
here, you guys?
>> That's real solid.
>> We go all the way across.
>> Right to there.
>> The best way to do it...
>> We got a team.
The first thing we want to do if
we wanted to be a team...
It wasn't five minutes, they
was six ideas on how to do
everything.
>> Are all six of
us going to go to sleep at
the same time?
>> Instead of going
there, we're going this way.
>> Yes.
>> Why don't we try to do
it right from the beginning?
You know? I'm not trying to be a
bitch, but it's like-- do it
right, babe.
I'm definitely vulnerable.
I'm the first one out...
because I'm the most outspoken.
>> What do you think?
>> Tom is weird.
What's he's worrying about the
... roof for?
Okay. Um, I'm okay now.
Let's grab that big one there...
>> All right.
>> ...and put it right
here, Rob.
>> We're putting it over here
now?
Now we're moving again?
I didn't know I was gonna be
again on the buffoon tribe, but
apparently I'm the brains behind
this operation, so I'm gonna
have to make it work somehow.
>> Saboga.
>> Is that a machete?
>> It is a machete.
>> Yay.
>> A map.
>> We are here and the
water is there.
>> First impression of the
group, I'm happy with the group.
You know, you got the mom, the
nice guy, the military guy, the
hot chick.
We're all going to play this
game, and we're all going to
battle for this prize, and it's
just, it's amazing that all
these different styles of play
are going to come together.
>> Rudy!
>> What do I look like,
Magellan?
( laughter )
>> I did this again
because it's part of my being.
It's not about the money for me.
It's all about life experiences.
And whenever I kick the bucket
one day, I am going out with a
casket full of life experiences.
>> Rupret?
>> Rupert.
>> Sorry. Rupert.
>> How are you getting there,
just cutting through here?
I'm the new guy on the block,
you know.
All these people know each
other.
>> Take a right.
>> Right now I'm just
trying to stand back and let all
these egos decide what we do and
I'll be the worker bee.
New strategy for a new game.
>> Rupert, look at this.
Holy cow!
We're in banana heaven!
>> We're in paradise.
>> We really are.
Okay, we have so many bananas,
but they're not quite ripe.
When we got on the boat and
I saw everybody, I was ecstatic.
Rupert and Jerri are in my
league.
Rudy, perfect ally.
Tina and Ethan, two winners.
Done.
It's so easy to convince the
others to vote off the two
winners.
>> Banana tree was a dead-
end trail.
We're following whatever trail
was by the banana tree.
>> I feel very vulnerable.
I did get put on a team
with a woman who doesn't like
me.
Tina is a huge concern of mine.
She didn't like me in Australia,
and I don't know necessarily if
she likes me now.
But I'm going to try this new
strategy of mine and that's just
to keep my damn mouth shut.
>> Lookit.
>> Yay.
>> Oh, yay.
>> Yes, that's very
good.
>> Oh, nice.
>> We did find our water
source but we can't drink it
right out of the well.
There's potential brain
parasites that will put you in a
coma, so it's not something to
be taken lightly.
>> Take a pot of water
back with us.
>> No, no, no, no.
We have to boil it, Rudy.
Five minutes, we have to boil
it.
>> We'll boil it, we'll boil it.
>> You know, I drank bad
water all over the world, in
Vietnam and Russia, and it never
bothered me.
I drank dirtier stuff than that.
>> I like this spot.
>> I like this spot for shelter.
>> This is my vote.
>> What do you think
about this, Kathy, for a house?
Give you all reasons.
There's a little breeze, but
we'll put the fire closer to the
water where there's even more
breeze 'cause that's where we'll
mostly be hanging out, I think.
>> I don't see why not.
As long as there's a breeze to
keep the bugs away.
>> We've got to have a
fire, and we've got to have a
shelter.
We know where the water is.
>> You guys get bamboo...
>> We're going to bring,
yeah, building materials as far
as bamboo.
I think I'd be lying if I said
there wasn't a day that went by,
since being in Africa, that I
didn't think at some point, even
if it was just for a moment,
about Survivor and about the
game and about the possibility
of coming back one day.
>> We can use that tree
and the "Y" there and lay one
beam in there and that will be
the high side.
It'll angle this way.
We don't need it any higher than
that.
It's never been done before.
No one's ever gone back to play
this game twice.
It changes the game completely,
not from a physical standpoint
but psychologically we know how
bad gets and we know how long
this road is.
It'll be interesting to see
who's up for that.
Are you guys all cool with this
thing?
>> No, that's fine, yeah.
>> I just can't
believe we're here.
Like, we're such morons.
You left everything you love to
come starve and have no water,
have no fire.
Seriously, we've got issues.
>> I know they're making
alliances.
>> I told you it was
going to be them against us.
>> It's the guys and the
girls, totally.
I totally know it.
>> Hey.
>> Yeah?
>> Those girls are
plotting, honey.
Hope you aren't plotting with
them.
>> No, we didn't
get into anything, honestly.
>> People are a little
bit paranoid and that's a good,
good state to have them in.
Suppose I ought to be as well,
but...
>> The guys have got some
scheme.
You can feel it.
>> I think Colby and
Lex are, like... Richard...
>> I think they are.
I think they are. I really do.
There is a girl thing that got
manifested, and so we were
talking about it.
And did we even think of doing a
360 to look around if anybody
was listening?
>> Let's talk about
that since I was sitting in the
woods listening to the girl
power.
( laughs )
>> There is too much girl power.
So our alliance wasn't too good.
So with that, we just aired out
all our dirty laundry.
>> Boys, I told them
what I heard about the girl
power and they think we got boy
power going.
>> You know what?
Let's just call a time-out...
>> I agree.
>> We have so much time to
do that later.
Let's just have a good time now.
Let's win challenges when we
have to win challenges and let's
get a comfortable shelter going.
>> I don't trust any of
you sons of guns.
>> I don't trust any of you!
>> I don't care whether
you're a man, or woman.
I don't trust you.
>> Let's just
win and then we won't talk about
this for another...
>> We can definitely put
this on the back burner for a
while, can't we?
>> Survivor: All-Stars
is a different game and I'm
figuring out how to play it.
So I've really got to push and
probe and stir the pot a little.
I'm just a big-ass target,
Doesn't matter what I do.
Just going to keep shaking
things up a little bit.
>> Richard, do you
know where we can find a rock
that might start the fire with a
knife?
>> A rock against
steel, you think?
>> Oh, are you naked?
>> Wouldn't that be shocking?
>> It would be shocking.
Yeah, he's naked. Okay.
>> All right, we'll be back.
>> That's enough.
This is off to an interesting
start.
>> There it goes.
>> This it is.
>> Keep going.
This is it.
>> Come on!
Come on!
( grunting )
>> All right.
>> We have to be able to
boil the water.
The first tribe in this game
that gets water and fire is a
tribe that's going to go the
farthest.
>> This is burning hot.
Burning.
>> I've so been where
you're at right now.
I did it for two days in Borneo.
I can't do fire. I have tried.
>> All right, there's
that positive attitude we're
looking for.
>> I killed myself
probably three hours each day to
try to start a fire.
You guys have just started.
>> So far, Sue has yet to
help us on the fire.
She says, "I can't do it."
Wherever...
Borneo, where the hell they went
last time.
Well, this ain't last time.
This is this time.
>> I am not going to let
myself even get close to
dehydration because it's hard to
bring yourself back from it,
especially in this kind of
situation.
Got to drink it.
I lived in Canada for six years
and I drank the water right out
of the lakes.
Right out of the lakes.
No filter system, nothing.
The way I see it, I drank enough
beaver poop in my life that my
body can handle what might be
growing in there, eh?
>> You drank the water
from the well?
>> Yeah.
>> Without boiling it?
>> Rob, I've probably
dranken worse water.
>> How much of it did you drink?
>> I drank four big coconut...
I left the coconut shell up
there.
It's, like, three-quarters of a
coconut shell.
>> Can anybody say "dumb ass"?
>> I drank four of 'em.
I actually got too full.
I wanted to drink more, but I'm
too full.
>> That's a lot, Sue.
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what Sue is up to.
If you get sick and you have to
check out of this game, you're
leaving five other people
here to do the job of six.
>> If she's going to drink
it, she's going to drink it.
>> If it's going to kill
her, I don't want to leave her
half dead because it will be a
... mess.
>> It would stink.
And we'll have to clean it.
>> It'll be like a corpse.
>> Got smoke, got smoke,
got smoke.
Some smoke.
>> Come on.
>> I can't.
I can't.
We're all dying of thirst.
We need fire.
My head's ready to pop.
We need to be able to boil
water.
We could be like Rudy and just
grab the water and drink it, but
none of us want to die.
>> It's burning my fingers.
>> We're so close.
( Ethan grunting )
>> We tried with the
fire plow forever.
Nothing happened.
We got a curl of smoke and we
were like cavemen, but that's
not fire.
>> Once you work this bow,
it causes friction.
A lot more friction than that
way, you know?
I mean, if you want to do it the
right way, this is the way.
>> Well, so that didn't work.
>> Nope.
>> I mean, unless God
strikes a log around here with
lightning, we might never get
fire.
>> We definitely need
something right now to give us
some hope.
I think everybody's starting to
feel a little...
>> Feel worried.
Not a little. Feel worried.
>> I'm glad I'm not alone.
>> No, you're not alone.
I'm worried as hell.
>> We've been given
nothing, and the realization of
it has now hit home.
No one's going to come in and
save us.
We have to save ourselves.
( Rupert sighs )
>> You know what I think?
Me and you ought to think about
an alliance.
>> You're a man of your word,
too from what a know of you.
I am, too.
Rudy looks at me and the first
time he sees me, you know, all
tie-dyed and hippie, he looked
right through it and wanted to
be my buddy.
>> Tina and Ethan are good
buddies.
>> I know.
>> The other two are good
buddies.
>> I know.
>> We could be out of this
thing in a hurry.
>> Yup.
>> I figured me and Rupert
ought to protect ourselves and
form an alliance, and that's all
we did.
He says, "I can depend on you,"
and he says, "You can depend on
me."
That's all I got to hear.
>> You and I are going
to be strong to the end.
>> Yeah.
>> Rudy is a man of few
words, but from what I gathered,
he's a man of honor.
If he and I stick together, if
we can just make it through
these first few days, he and I
will stick together through the
end of the game.
>> I'm dying.
I didn't sleep at all last
night.
Every two seconds, rolling over,
getting bit, I don't think I can
do another night like that.
>> No.
>> I am beat right now.
>> You know what?
I don't want to do another night
like that.
>> Last night was by far
the worst night I've ever spent
in a Survivor.
I would have built a shelter
completely differently.
I'm in construction.
I know what I'm doing.
>> Once we get fire, we
can make everything else happen.
That's the thing.
>> That's the thing.
>> We got our shelter, good.
I don't even want to think about
that shelter until we have fire.
I don't even care about it.
I'll sleep on the beach if I
have to, but we need to have
fire to get some water at this
point.
>> I'm more than willing
to work on the fire issue, but
all aspects of our shelter
should have been created
differently.
These flat pieces are no good.
>> It's my back and my
shoulders and arms touching the
wood.
>> And the sand.
>> Yeah.
>> There are six people
here without water.
Two people are more concerned
about the bottom of the shelter
because they're not comfortable
at night sleeping.
There's not one person here that
doesn't understand that you two
have not been able to sleep.
Six people haven't had water.
That's what I'm thinking.
>> We've been busting
our ass trying to make fire
since we got here, since day
one.
>> You keep giving up on it,
though.
>> Every single day.
We haven't been giving up.
We're physically exhausted.
We're dehydrated.
>> Don't yell.
>> I'm not yelling, I'm just
saying call it like it is.
>> I am calling it like it is.
We just talked about it.
We all are calling it like it
is.
>> I'm not going through
another night over here with no
sleep, that's all.
>> I was sleeping in the
same thing you guys were.
>> We didn't sleep, though.
>> I never heard so much
cry baby, titty sucking in all
my life.
We bitched about the clothes,
we bitched about the weather,
and we bitched that God ain't
give us no water.
We're going to have to toughen
up a little bit.
>> Are you two happy with this?
>> Yeah because we don't
want to do it again.
>> Thank you. That's all
I care about, really.
'Cause I have been able to
sleep.
I want you guys to be able to
>> What can I say about Alicia?
She's a drama queen.
You want the fact, you come to
Mariano, you get it as it is.
She's a drama queen.
>> Let's start this
freaking fire.
Somebody has to say something.
They can't just do that.
Who made Rob the master of this
camp and Amber his little
in-pocket girl?
When did that happen?
>> What do you think?
You want to make an alliance and
cover our own asses?
>> I don't know if I can take
you seriously or not.
>> I'm being 100% serious.
Just we can't make it obvious at
all.
Like, I'm carrying logs with you
right now.
It's got to end.
>> Right.
>> All right?
>> All right.
>> Do you want to?
>> Yeah.
>> Amber and I have an
alliance for obvious reasons.
She's beautiful, obviously, any
idiot can see that.
But I'll keep my word no matter
what to her.
I trust her.
I don't think she's going to
screw me.
>> Switch up.
That thing is so hot.
Do you want me to take over?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, all-stars.
Boy, that's the kicker.
I think within the last 24
hours we've all questioned, at
least half a dozen times, why in
the world we signed up for this.
>> Maybe there's
something in there.
>> I'm running out of steam.
>> Yeah, I think I
could start the fire without
even blinking.
But they don't need to know
that.
( laughs )
But I have no interest in
trying.
Look at how skinny they all are.
They'll be dying in no time.
I'm fine.
I'm not even hungry.
I'm playing that one by ear.
They could think I'm just cocky
and arrogant and think I could
last the whole game.
Hmm, imagine that.
>> Sorry I'm not very helpful.
>> No worries.
If you don't feel well, save
yourself in case we have a
challenge.
>> And I'm just
frickin' busy, so I'll get to
you when I get a chance.
>> Richard is totally obnoxious.
He's going out of his way to not
do any work.
I think Richard wants to stand
out.
I think Richard wants to be
special in our group.
It's just part of his strategy
to kind of be like a little bit
shocking, like "I don't really
care what happens..."
>> Man, when we... when we
get to the players splitting
this... splitting these things,
and we need more chopping...
>> Cool.
>> ...you know, then you
can help.
( pounding continues )
Richard Hatch was the very first
person to win Survivor, ever.
He spent the last couple, three
years since he won Survivor
talking about how he is just the
best this game has ever seen.
>> I love the fact
that he's just, you know...
>> Lounging, lounging.
>> Lounging in his
birthday suit.
He is the king!
>> He was the king when he
was playing with a bunch of
sheep.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That's true.
That's true.
>> That was like shooting
fish in a barrel.
( laughs )
This is a whole 'nother thing
altogether.
>> He's the prototype
for all of us other survivors,
so of course everyone wants him
down.
Everyone wants to dethrone the
king.
I mean, are you doing this,
like, alone thing on purpose?
'Cause it...
>> Kind of.
Um, I'm off by myself so people
can see I'm not...
Yeah, you guys can be all
talking together.
Four of you went off into the
woods while I was out floating.
>> Yeah, but we
weren't talking about anything.
>> Maybe, but you know
what I mean?
I can't know that.
>> Sure.
>> And have at it, you know?
>> I personally
think... what fun would it be if
the king left the first day?
It wouldn't be any fun.
>> Ah, tree mail.
We just got our first tree mail
today, a little earlier than
expected.
But I guess today is just as
good as any day, being that
we'll probably just be thirstier
tomorrow.
Well, I've got some good news
and some bad news.
>> Uh-oh.
>> The good news is,
I've got another pole for us to
sleep on.
This is the bad news.
>> What's bad about that?
That's good.
>> Hey, you want to read
it as a group?
>> Sue, you want to come over?
>> Just speak up.
>> Probably start it now.
>> Just speak up!
>> "To and from each
challenge, fly your colors as
you stride.
In a show of unity-- unity--
your flag shows tribal pride.
Three more days are guaranteed
for those triumphant in the
game.
Bring your dive mask with you to
face the man of flame."
That must be Richard Hatch.
>> Just got our tree
mail, our first free mail.
And it seems to be an immunity
challenge, but we're hoping with
an immunity challenge, we can
win some fire, 'cause our tribe
is, uh... we're hurtin' pretty
bad.
>> It is killing me not
knowing who else is here.
Every freaking survivor could be
here.
I don't know, and I can't wait
to find out.
>> PROBST: Chapera, come on in.
What's going on?
( laughing )
>> We want to ask you
that question.
>> Yeah, seriously.
We want to know.
>> PROBST: You want to see who
you're playing against?
>> Yeah.
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo, come on
in.
More familiar faces.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Hi.
>> PROBST: Any surprises so far?
Hatch, surprised to see anybody
over here from Chapera?
>> Count them gone,
Jeff, count them gone.
One, two, gone!
Who are they? Egh!
>> PROBST: He hasn't changed at
all, has he, Sue?
>> People, ready to leave!
>> His team looks like
they love him already.
( laughing )
>> PROBST: Well, 12 survivors
would be nice.
Two tribes would be fun.
Not enough.
Saboga, come on in.
>> Ooh...
>> Oh-ho!
>> Rupert!
>> The big man in the
back, there he is.
All right. Game on!
>> PROBST: All right, here we
are.
Survivor: All-Stars.
So, tell me about arriving at
beach.
Big Tom, what'd you find when
you got to camp?
>> Nothin'.
>> Just a knife and
machete, a machete.
>> Oh, yeah, and a bucket.
>> PROBST: You got a machete?
>> Yeah, and a bucket.
>> PROBST: What else, Hatch?
>> We got a pot.
>> PROBST: Rudy, did you get a
map to water?
>> A map to water, a
machete and a bucket.
And we can't drink the water.
>> PROBST: Why?
>> 'Cause we don't have fire.
>> PROBST: You don't have fire?
>> No.
>> PROBST: How about Chapera?
>> PROBST: Hatch, I know you
have fire.
Nobody has fire?
>> No we haven't got it yet.
>> No fire.
>> We got smoke.
>> PROBST: So, as Rudy says, the
water's of no value.
>> Well...
>> I drank it.
>> PROBST: Navy SEAL, how wise
is that?
Is that all right?
>> Yeah.
( laughing )
>> PROBST: So, is it wise
because it's the other tribe?
>> Yeah.
( laughter )
>> There you go.
( laughing )
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to your first immunity
challenge.
It harkens back to the very
first challenge we ever did on
Survivor, "Quest for Fire."
Here's how it works.
You will each start on floating
platforms.
On my "go," you will dive down
and release your raft from a
mooring on the bottom of the
ocean floor.
You'll then take the fire
torches on your raft and use
them to light a series of woks,
making your way back toward the
beach.
Once you get to the beach, light
a third wok.
And then you'll drag your raft
under a bamboo crawl.
First two tribes to light their
final wok and cross the finish
line with all six members both
win immunity.
Now, for the immunity idol.
It's two pieces.
A human being.
Environment.
Each piece grants immunity.
First two tribes to cross the
finish win a piece of the idol.
If you hold part of this
immunity idol, you cannot go to
Tribal Council, you cannot be
voted out of this game.
You ready to get this going?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Swim on out, wait for
my "go."
>> Here we go.
>> Go, guys.
>> PROBST: Richard Hatch just
got naked!
Survivor: All-Stars is
officially on.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Got to get your raft untied
before you can move on.
Two clips to untie the raft.
Chapera is first out of the
block.
Moving toward their woks.
Mogo Mogo right behind them.
Saboga struggling.
( indistinct voices )
Chapera and Mogo Mogo-- neck and
neck.
>> Keep going. Yeah, baby!
( grunts )
>> We're almost there.
Pull.
>> PROBST: Chapera working their
way over to the first wok.
Mogo Mogo heading to their first
wok.
>> You got it, Lex.
>> We're almost there.
>> That's okay.
>> Go, go!
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo has their
first wok lit.
Chapera has their first wok lit.
Saboga, still struggling.
>> Come on, guys, get
me over there.
>> Go, Jenna, go!
>> Go!
( indistinct voices )
( grunting )
>> PROBST: Saboga has their
first wok lit.
>> You got it, Jenna, you got
it.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo and Chapera
still dead even.
( indistinct shouting )
Lex, swimming over to light the
second wok for Mogo Mogo.
Big Tom lighting the second wok
for Chapera.
>> Come on, Jenna!
>> PROBST: Jenna lights the
second wok for Saboga.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Saboga, closing the
gap.
Mogo Mogo first ashore.
Chapera right on their tail.
>> Go, go, push.
Push, guys.
>> PROBST: Fatigue starting to
set in.
Raft is heavy, water tough.
Mogo Mogo with the slight lead.
( indistinct voices )
Mogo Mogo has their third wok
lit.
( indistinct voices )
Chapera has their third wok lit.
>> Okay, Jenna.
( indistinct voices )
>> Go, go.
>> PROBST: First two tribes to
finish win immunity.
Everybody and every piece of the
raft has to go under the bamboo
crawl.
Let's go, Saboga, pick it up.
( shouting )
Saboga's closed the gap.
They're back in it.
>> I can't get the fire out!
I can't get the fire out!
Ethan!
>> Push!
( indistinct voices )
>> One, two, three. Push!
Go! Go! Go!
>> Lift!
( grunting and shouting )
>> PROBST: Chapera, the first
tribe to win immunity.
>> Whoo!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo not there
yet.
Mogo Mogo and Saboga still
fighting for that second
immunity.
( grunting )
>> Light it!
Lex, light it!
>> Pick it up, pick it up.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo has their
last torch lit.
( grunts )
Mogo Mogo wins immunity.
( indistinct shouts )
>> Whoo!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Chapera,
congratulations.
Immunity.
No Tribal Council.
You're out here three more days.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo...
immunity.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Safe from Tribal
Council.
Out here at least three more
days.
>> Mogo!
>> Mogo Mogo!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Not a happy group.
Tough to lose the first
challenge.
Tribal Council tomorrow night.
One of you six will be the first
All-Star voted out.
You have tonight and tomorrow to
figure out who that's going to
be.
You can head back to camp.
Chapera, 'cause you crossed
first, you get the honor of
lighting up Burning Man.
( cheering )
>> All right!
>> Yeah!
>> Nice job.
>> Very good job.
>> We won that.
We played as a team.
>> Team.
We have to stay as a team.
All right? Never mind
what's going on back here.
When we had to pull it together
and get it done, we got it done.
Let's go, Chapera!
Let's go! Good job!
( whooping )
We're the biggest bunch of
misfit survivors you could put
together from seven seasons, and
we go out there and win it.
Nobody's expecting us to get it
done.
We are the ultimate underdogs.
>> Wasn't that the coolest?
>> That was the best.
>> We didn't win.
We came in first place of the
very first All-Star Challenge.
>> Immunity challenge.
>> We came back with a
good attitude... but we still
have no fire.
>> Ya!
>> It's horrible
being the first group to Tribal
Council, horrible.
None of us came out here to be
the first one voted off, but one
of us is going to be the first
one voted off.
Tonight I think it's important
we take out the two winners
first.
I don't want to see them get
another million dollars.
I just want to get rid of them
at the beginning.
>> And I hate to say it, but...
it's going to feel good.
>> It's gonna feel great.
>> ...good, because
they don't know what it's like.
>> No, they don't.
Hey, Rupert?
>> I don't know.
>> I don't know Rupert well
enough to know if I can trust
him.
He could be playing a bigger
game than I think.
Everything's a game.
You can't take anything anyone
says for what it means.
You're a very strong member of
the tribe, but you're also a
winner, Ethan.
>> I know, but that's the...
that's your best advantage.
>> No. It's not.
>> You got to be silly now to
bring a winner to the
final two.
>> I just don't want
you and Tina around, 'cause
you're winners.
>> You honestly think that?
>> Yeah.
Nobody out here wants to reward
another winner.
Sorry, guys, it's our game now.
Get the hell off our playing
field.
>> Whatever you do, vote
for Jenna tonight.
We'd have a better chance
tonight to vote Jenny... Jenna.
I think Ethan and I need to
stick together, because if we
are the first two targets, we
need to be trying to figure out
for ourself, well, what can we
do as targets to stay in the
game.
What to do, what to do.
What's a mother to do?
Hopefully, we can pull Rupert in
and kind of surprise everybody
tonight.
>> You got Jerri and
Jenna on one side saying, "We
got to get rid of the winners."
I got Tina and Ethan on the
other side saying, "You cannot
trust Jerri and Jenna.
You cannot trust them."
I think I might have some
control over Rudy's vote.
He and I are going to stick
together.
( thunder crashing )
>> PROBST: Welcome to a very wet
Tribal Council.
It's a tree house suspended in
the middle of a jungle.
A bit of a climb-- not one
you're gonna want to make often.
Go ahead and grab a torch behind
you.
Approach the flame. Get fire.
Because I know you know by now,
fire represents life on the
island and definitely in this
game.
Once you have fire, put it back
in its slot and have a seat.
Well, it is the rainy season in
Panama, so this could be a sign
of things to come for the next
36 days.
How do the first three days out
here compare to what you've been
through in the past, Jerri?
>> It's total hell.
( laughing )
>> PROBST: Rupert, you just
barely got home, and you turn
around to come out here and do
it again.
( thunder crashing )
Sorry you made that decision?
>> You know, there's a
little piece of me that says,
why in the hell did I come back
here?
I got to think about my wife and
my daughter.
I did this for Laura and Reya.
Maybe I can do better this time.
>> PROBST: I'm noticing that
Jerri is literally collecting
water while we sit here and
slurping it.
>> It's bad, Jeff, it's bad.
You can live without food, but
you cannot live without water,
and we are all feeling it right
now, and it's scary.
It's really scary.
>> PROBST: Are you trying to
collect water in that?
>> Yeah. It ends up
being a spigot.
>> PROBST: Rudy, how does this
tribe stack up against Chapera
and Mogo Mogo?
>> We got a good bunch of
people.
I'm 75, I ain't what a used to
be.
I wish I was 23, but I'm not...
But these guys are all...
they're good.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
liabilities.
Rudy, you mentioned yours--
you're 75-- although you're
better than most 50-year-olds.
Ethan, what's a drawback for
you?
What's gonna hurt you in this
game?
>> I think, um, having
won a game before may hurt me.
>> PROBST: Is one of the reasons
that being a winner hurts you is
that people respect the fact
that you've won this game and
therefore are dangerous?
>> Definitely, you know?
In addition to that, a lot of
it's payback time, you know?
"You won again.
You had your shot."
>> PROBST: Jenna, can you find a
scenario in your head that could
include a final two that has a
winner and a nonwinner and you
want to vote for the winner?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Really?
>> I wouldn't, no.
>> PROBST: You've already
decided?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Best player may not
win, then, from your point of
view.
>> No.
>> PROBST: Just based on
irritation.
>> Just based on a
million dollars.
It's a lot easier for the
winners to come back and say
they're here for competition,
because they've got a bank
account that has $1 million.
>> PROBST: Tina, is that fair?
>> Of course not, but we
all... all the winners who came
back knew that coming in.
We all knew that we would have
big targets on our chest.
>> PROBST: Rupert, does it
matter to you if somebody has
won this game before or not?
>> You know, I-I like to
think I would vote for the best
person out there.
>> PROBST: How about for you,
Rudy?
>> If they can do it
again, let them go.
>> You know, look at any sports
team in any league around
the world.
Some teams win the championship
every year.
Should they be knocked out at
the beginning of the season
'cause of the fact that they won
the championship that one year?
No.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Ethan, you're up.
>> Jenna, Jenna, Jenna.
Your mouth just keeps going and
going and going.
But you better be careful,
'cause it might bite you in that
big old butt of yours.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final, and
the person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Jenna.
That's two votes Jenna.
Tina.
One vote Tina.
Two votes Tina,
two votes Jenna.
That's three votes Tina,
First person voted out of
Survivor: All-Stars...
Tina, could you bring me your
torch.
Tina, the tribe has spoken.
Because you do not yet have fire
back at the camp, you won't be
taking your torches back with
you.
They will stay here until you
have made fire on your own.
You guys can head back.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
Everyone is desperate for water.
>> Dehydration may be our
biggest concern.
>> These people are like animals
gone wild.
>> PROBST: And Ethan tries to
prove his worth.
>> Are you going to
see if you could catch fish?
>> I'm struggling out here.
I'm trying to find my niche.
>> Ethan came up empty-handed.
>> Rupert goes out.
Five minutes later, he comes
back with a fish. Great.
>> No one wants to be the
first person voted off, and
especially me, being a
competitor, but I was only here
three days.
And was it a hard three days?
Absolutely.
This experience has been
different for me, because I went
in on an equal playing ground
the first time, so, you know, I
kind of expected it, but it
doesn't make it any easier.