>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Four days without fire or water
took its toll.
>> Dehydration may be our
biggest concern.
>> PROBST: A mystery box with
three locks was discovered at
tree mail.
>> Oh-oh.
We see a big crate.
We have no idea what's inside.
>> It feels like something
substantial, whatever it is.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, Ethan led Saboga to a
comeback.
>> Saboga wins reward!
The reward was a choice
between blankets or flint to
make fire and a clue to the
first key of their lockbox,
which they learned contained
rice.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: There's a rub.
If you choose the flint, Mogo
Mogo gets it, as well as
Chapera.
>> SUSAN: ( laughs )
>> PROBST: Saboga chose the
flint and gave all three tribes
fire.
>> Fire! Yay!
>> PROBST: At Saboga...
>> My foot sort of makes
me limp a little.
>> Rudy's not doing okay.
His feet-- he did something to
the bone inside.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Saboga faced another
setback...
Saboga's still bailing water!
When they finish a distant
third.
For the second straight time,
Saboga going to Tribal Council.
Rudy's injury and Ethan's status
as a previous winner put both of
them on the chopping block.
But when the votes came in, it
was Rudy who took the fall.
Rudy, the tribe has spoken.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by CBS
PARAMOUNT TELEVISION NETWORK
>> Bug bites are bad.
And, you know, my problem is
that I couldn't resist the urge
to scratch them.
It was more than I could bear,
and now I'm definitely paying
for it because I think that
they get way, way worse when
you scratch them.
They raise up and they become
kind of like little open sores,
open wounds.
And then the salt water gets
into them and it feels like
fire.
It's horrible.
>> Honey, you're going to get
scars.
>> I'm not scratching them.
I'm just rubbing.
Ugh!
This is bad.
They're like bug bites on top of
bug bites on top of...
We look like freaks.
Bigger freaks than we already
are.
>> You cannot be itching
yourself, girl.
We talked about that.
>> I can't stop myself.
>> You just have to, like,
endure about half an hour of...
>> Itchiness?
>> ...itchiness, and then
it won't itch anymore.
>> This is like the
hardest thing I've ever done
to not itch right now.
>> Your arms are messed up now.
>> I hate everything right now.
Not you guys, but I want to go
home.
>> Oh, God, Jenna.
>> Jenna's hurting.
Jenna wants to go home.
Um, first of all, Jenna's not
eating.
I don't know what that's all
about.
You know, I think that first
four days where we had no water
and no food really put her body
into a tailspin where she's
feeling it today.
And now she's not even drinking
enough.
I have to push her to drink.
She won't go in the water to
cool her body down.
She's just not taking
directions.
She's kind of a wandering
zombie.
>> It seems to be tough for
her this time around.
>> Yeah, it's tough.
>> Especially mentally.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I don't think she's happy.
>> She's really not.
She's really not happy.
>> We're going to dig
some holes and bury these like
this and sit that on top.
>> I don't know exactly
what has got into the tribe.
This morning, they want to do
stuff.
It's a little bit of missing
Rudy, a little bit of guilt, a
little everything.
There's a lot of nervous energy.
It's getting everybody going.
>> Without being
overconfident or cocky, I'm
feeling really good about where
we're at.
Yay!
>> That's cute.
>> The four of us left
in this tribe are family, and we
work really well together.
>> Oh, another little one.
>> A little guy.
Better than eating them damn
snails.
>> Where'd you find that guy?
>> Right there.
>> All right, try this out.
( Rupert chuckling )
>> As soon as I brought
the fish back, Ethan's grabbing
his spear and running out there.
( chuckles )
I tried to tell him it's not a
competition.
It's really not.
>> I hope he catches something.
That'd be good for his ego.
>> I mean, those
triggerfish swim into a nook.
You just got to jab them.
>> You jab 'em.
>> Just couldn't do it.
>> You'll get better.
I like being the fisherman.
I know he wants to be, too, but
it can't be a competition
between he and I.
It will just hurt his emotions.
It will hurt the whole camp.
That's what beat us at the
challenge yesterday.
We weren't working together.
If we can keep this harmony up,
we will be a strong little
tribe.
Even though we're little, we
are going to be mighty.
>> It was low tide early enough
in the morning, and I figured,
"Here's my shot.
I'm going to go get something
for breakfast."
I really want to get one of
these rays.
There are some enormous
stingrays out there.
And I saw a couple, but I
couldn't get to 'em in time.
I have no fins and it's very,
very difficult.
Never mind a spear that's as
blunt as you can imagine.
But I was determined to get some
good food and roast it.
You bring in a fish, you get
some smiles.
I eventually found a shark under
a ledge, and I wanted him.
So I said screw it.
Let the spears float.
Just look at it, just gauge the
situation.
Just kept thinking, "How am I
going to do this?
How am I going to do this?"
Screw it.
I'm not leaving the thing there.
I'm going home with food.
He starts thrashing.
Tight up against the rock.
As long as he was trying to stay
lodged in there and I didn't
move my hand, but wouldn't let
him go, I felt okay.
Kept breathing.
Going up, breathing, holding on,
breathing.
Trying to get enough energy to
think what I'm going to do.
So I grabbed my spear and
figured I'd try to get through
his belly.
( gasps )
I let the head part go for a
second and whomp-- shark bite!
And I poke him in the eye.
He takes another chunk deeper.
There was no way.
He was not letting go.
He was never letting go.
I spent the next-- I don't
know-- half hour like that,
trying to figure out what am I
going to do to get this thing
off?
So I swim, no fins, nothing,
just kind of backwards swimming
as close as I can to shore to
get onto a rock.
Get onto a rock and pound the
side of his head with a rock
until he lets go.
Yi-yi-yi-yi.
>> Oh, my God.
>> His teeth, right there.
He's got me.
Pull it.
I let go a little bit, he goes
whomp, for the second bite.
Bites in further and harder.
So what do I do?
I bite him.
>> Oh, my God! Richard!
>> Can you see the bite marks?
>> Is it possible to call
a gay man a stud?
I think you're a stud.
>> Yeah, you're a provider.
>> If you're going to
stay on my arm, it's like this.
>> No way anybody else
is catching fish like that.
Richard Hatch is a fishing god.
He bit a shark that bit him.
I mean, it's so...
It's like man versus nature.
It's so Hemingway-esque.
I love it.
>> He's impressive.
>> He's very impressive.
I mean, he may not be impressive
downstairs, but he's very
impressive in other ways.
( Richard chuckling )
>> You know, you're at
the point without food for
whatever it's been, seven days.
People are ready to eat.
I need to be the provider.
They are just loving me right
now and it's good.
He bit me-- I ate him.
Mm.
>> Oh, mama mia, we-a
having a-some a-good food.
>> I've reached my daily
limit of giving thanks to
Richard Hatch.
>> And they go on and on and on:
"Thanks, Richard, thanks,
Richard, thanks, Richard."
Little baby bye-byes, Richard,
real soon.
( laughs )
>> Want to go check tree mail?
>> Okay.
>> Wait for me.
>> Okay, come on.
>> Oh, my God, you guys.
Home Depot box?
Okay, ready?
Drum roll.
>> Spears.
>> Oh, my God!
>> We got to build...
>> Okay, hold on. Hold on.
"Dream it, design it, do it.
Remodel your home in just one
day."
How perfect.
>> Basically, it's a
contest to see who can build the
best home for themselves in a
24-hour period.
>> "Make it bigger,
stronger, better.
Creativity and structure come
into play.
These tools should come in
handy.
Use driftwood, palm or kelp.
Only four tribemates can
participate.
You can do it. We can help."
>> "Tomorrow you'll be
judged by a professional to keep
it fair from bush guide, a much
better night's sleep for the
winners will be dropped down
from the air."
Mattresses, mosquito nets.
Ours is going to be a
disaster, I can tell you that
right now.
>> Ah, now see? There we go.
We've got a good group...
>> You know what we need?
Take that tree out in the
middle...
No, the tree comes out in the
middle.
Why? Why? I'm taking it out.
>> After we fight, you will.
Sue, she's a hag from hell.
>> Where do I have a beam
in the middle of my house,
just sitting there?
>> You got it in every corner.
>> Yeah, connected to a wall.
>> How I made it to 48
without Sue Hawk leading me by
the hand is a mystery.
>> Tom...
>> You do your half,
I'll do my half thing.
>> The tree's coming down, Tom.
>> You can do it then.
>> I will.
>> I'll sit out if y'all
want me to.
>> No.
>> She's the bossiest
woman I've ever been around.
There ain't no doubt in my
mind, her elevator don't go to
the top floor.
>> Why you walking fast now?
>> Huh?
>> "First place reward
and key clue number two.
Second place only key clue
number two."
Only four people are allowed
to work on this though.
>> This is what I do.
>> Yeah, this is what you do.
>> You have to do this.
>> Yeah, this is your job.
>> I'm going to sit out.
Actually, it's not hard for me
to sit on the sideline and
bite my tongue, because just
in my head I just keep
repeating, "These are really
stupid people I'm with."
They are. They're so stupid.
I hope they don't get jacked off
of this challenge just to
bring them down a notch.
>> Who else is sitting out?
>> I'll sit out.
>> Amber's sitting out, okay.
>> You guys trust me
enough to give you guys a plan
and we go by it...
>> Yeah, you're a construction
worker.
>> ...and just do it and
don't...
>> This is all about you.
>> I'm in construction
and I love to build things if
I have tools.
I was right up and at it, and
I was pumped and I was, like,
"Yeah, this is for me.
This is my challenge.
We'll win this."
One foot.
How high do you want the floor
up?
>> A foot.
To be honest with you, I was
so into what we were doing.
>> Down a hair, Tom.
>> We had a basic floor
plan and then got going.
It clicked, and we never
slowed down.
>> We got to get a
creative aspect to this.
If you guys want to try to
make a deck there or
something, a flower garden...
>> When I signed up to
take part in the reward
challenge, I thought that I'd
be, being a big help to Boston
Rob and Big Tom, but the guys
delegated me to go work with
Alicia.
>> I didn't even try
to get in there on that one.
>> Yeah, this is...
>> I knew that was going to
happen.
>> That's the story of
my Survivor life, that, uh,
the big boys don't let me
play.
>> And we got five
foot and three quarter.
So that's got to come out.
Easy.
That's square right there.
>> In the beginning,
the flirting with Boston Rob
was complete strategy for me,
and on the other end, I
thought it was complete
strategy for him, too.
And I'll admit, when I saw him
building that shelter, he was
pretty hot building that
shelter.
He's good at doing what he
does.
It's getting much easier and
easier to flirt with Boston
Rob, for sure.
>> Alicia thinks she's
this architect for some Zen
company or something.
Her vision is about as deep
as... yeah, that's about how
deep it is.
Where's Cesternino?
>> You know what, he's
strolling.
I don't know.
>> Cesternino, I
think, is useless all around.
Seems like he's on a never-
ending coffee break.
>> Where have you been?
>> I went to go grab
something, but it was too
heavy to get it all the way
back.
Yeah, and then I got lost in
the jungle.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to
disappear like that.
>> It gets frustrating
because Rob Cesternino does
the minimal to get by.
And you know what?
Everybody noticed it.
>> Want to go get more
rocks or you want to hammer...
>> You want to get more rocks.
>> Okay.
>> That heat is
excruciating, and I've been
making, like, 20 trips to get
those rocks here, so have at
it, sweetie pie.
>> I wonder what
they're planning on making.
I don't get the gist of it
from Rupert.
>> Just logs, that's
all I hear.
>> I'm a rehabber by
trade, and that's what I do is
work on houses, so I told my
tribe we're building a log
cabin.
We're going to dig down into
the sand a couple feet to add
to our height, so you walk
into it and you'll be able to
stand up.
That's what I want.
>> Personally, I don't
feel digging into the ground
is a good idea.
>> Okay.
So you want to build the thing
all out of the ground?
We need...
>> Yeah, I think it
makes more sense 'cause if we
get it moist, kind of
underground, we're totally...
>> Do we want to be an
eye-catcher, a pop, "Oh, my
God," or do we want to be like
everybody else?
>> Um, what I want is a
place I can actually sleep in.
Sounds to me like you're
really concerned about
something standing out, and I
love that, but...
>> None of them are
going to make a structure as
creative as ours.
They're going to make huts.
>> I hear you.
>> We're going to make a log
cabin.
>> Rupert's a complete control
freak.
He has to have everything his
way and he thinks he's the
only one who can do it right.
But you know what?
All we need is rain rushing
down the side of that hill
right into our shelter and
we're screwed.
The other thing is, it's
going to take longer to dig
three feet in the ground...
>> How do you have any idea?
I know what I can do.
I'm 40 years old.
I've done my ... for years.
I've built houses for 20 years.
>> I hear you.
Can we vote on it?
Does anyone else have any
concern?
>> Okay.
All right.
>> Then we should...
>> Then let's do it.
Let's just... do it.
Let's just do it.
>> Jerri and Rupert got
in a fight.
Perfect.
That's just what I wanted.
She had very valid points.
You know, I don't want to dig
down three feet, live under
the ground, but I'm not going
to say that 'cause if you piss
someone off, you know, you
could be going home.
>> We're going to make
the most amazing tree house
you've ever seen.
>> That's right.
>> As far as the, uh,
floor plan and building
scheme, we've got it up here.
We know it's all about
location, location, location.
>> Absolutely.
>> So, basically, we're
doing an elevated floor plan,
probably have a little balcony
out front, a kitchen area over
on the left...
>> A nap area down below.
And perhaps a little crow's
nest up top to just kind of go
up there and think and Zen
out.
>> Crow's nest, but as
we like to refer to it, The
Love Nest.
>> The Love Nest, indeed.
>> And when you've got
Richard Hatch on your team,
there's lots of love.
>> Oh, too much love.
>> Yeah.
>> Rock garden, swing, coconut
phone.
Um, what else is in a regular
house?
>> TV.
>> We're not making a TV.
Um...
>> There are six members of our
tribe 'cause we've never lost
anything, yet, so we had to sit
out two people.
And I happily sat out of that
one, 'cause that's a lot of
work.
So we've got Lex and, uh,
Colby building the shelter,
and Shii Ann and Jenna...
>> Ooh, it's hot.
>> Are "helping" build the
shelter.
( chuckles )
>> We've been writing some
creative things, but we thought
we'd just join you.
This is all nonstructural
stuff that I thought it would
be fun to add.
Rope ladder, a hammock, to
chisel our names or the Mogo
Mogo icon into it, um, a dumb
waiter, if we do a bi-level we
could have, like a pulley, um,
some sort of door or a rock
garden, um, a coconut phone
that would go from the top
floor to down, downstairs
phone.
This is all stuff if we have
time.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> And, like, palm beds.
>> We'll see.
I mean, all those touches...
>> Yeah, that's all...
>> The most important
thing is the structure itself.
>> It was as if when we spoke,
they couldn't hear it.
They had, like, their
transmitters tuned to each
other only.
>> We have to build this
thing extra tough, just
because we got a 250-pound
shark-catching gay fisherman.
>> Shark, shark wrangler.
>> That's right.
( hammering )
>> There's a lot of
other factors that come into
my game that may not come into
anybody else's game.
I mean, people have family
that they know when this is
over that they're going to be
there, you know?
That's all a question mark for
me.
I have a lot to lose being here.
Like, my mom.
That's a constant issue with me.
I'm wondering if I should have
left again.
>> We need to make rope.
>> Yeah, I'll get to that.
I'm busy right now lashing
this thing down; I'm all busy.
>> She's had cancer for a long
time and she's not better, and
I'm just afraid that she might
pass away while I'm here.
>> I can't tell if I like the
front or the back better.
>> That's curb appeal, babe.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my God, you
guys, this is getting dangerous.
>> Can't see anymore.
>> Rupert's idea was a
little ambitious.
We ended up working all
through the night.
We were trying to nail nails in
the pitch black.
And then in the middle of the
night, Rupert had dug half the
trench and I saw this giant
tree trunk down there, and you
can't chop it out.
>> My God.
I could not believe the
stupidity.
We played strong, but we
played stupid, and that is
what infuriates me.
>> Not good.
>> I don't think they're going
to disqualify us if...
>> If you just want to
be done, then stop and be done
and let me do.
I have a hard time standing
back and listening to a bunch
of people say it's too much
work, it can't get done.
Everybody's a "can't do it."
Everybody, everybody.
All three of them.
>> What are we going to
do for beds?
They're going to want to see a
shelter that's got...
>> Of course, we'll
need beds in here, of course.
>> Well then, take
it as a bed, I mean, that's...
>> We've crumbled.
In a single day, we went from a
happy group of four working
together, to three people not
knowing what the hell's going
on and one going completely
mad.
This is Rupert gone mad.
>> Looks good, you guys.
>> Yeah, put the welcome mat
out.
>> PROBST: What's going on, Mogo
Mogo?
>> Hello.
>> How 'bout that curb appeal?
>> PROBST: It's nice, although
this is the guy you want to
impress.
>> Hi.
>> PROBST: Brought along with me
Raffa, licensed contractor,
expert in construction, right
here from Panama.
He's going to visit each camp
and he will decide who has the
best shelter, so, take a look.
>> Kitchen area, where we like
to hang out, have our fireside
chats.
>> This is our outdoor balcony.
>> Hop up there, Lex.
>> This is our balcony for...
>> That's the balcony.
>> You can have an ocean view.
( rumbling and crackling )
>> Raffa, he starts
going around the shelter and
the first thing he does is
start grabbing on to things
and jerking them trying to rip
them down.
I don't know that Raffa
realizes, we got to live in
this shelter.
( talking over each other )
>> Woo, baby!
>> Yeah, shake it.
>> Look at him, yeah,
going up on the ladder.
>> Oh, geez.
>> Well, we know Richard
Hatch can now lay on it and
walk on it.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> Sure enough, he got
his level out, and he actually
gave me one of those, "Mm."
And that's a compliment, coming
from Raffa.
>> What do you think of that,
huh?
>> PROBST: That looks good.
>> Whoo!
>> I think he likes it.
I think he loves it.
>> Yeah, so...
Vamanos, vamanos.
>> Thank you.
>> Mi casa, su casa.
>> PROBST: No bribes.
>> No bri...
>> PROBST: He's past bribery.
What's going on, Chapera?
( shouting )
>> Get my remote, Jeff, and
let's watch something.
>> PROBST: I brought along
Raffa.
We'll take a tour.
>> Yeah?
>> PROBST: Location, yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Okay, I want to show him
something.
These are all undermined, dug
in and square.
>> You're not moving this.
>> These are three foot in
the ground, and that-- all this
is square.
>> JEFF: Fuerte?
>> Strong, it's strong.
>> Tell him to hop up on
the swing.
>> Come on, buddy.
It's not going anywhere.
Want to swing?
>> Thank you, thank you.
>> Whee!
>> That's okay.
>> All right!
>> We will persuade you.
>> Look at all these rocks.
This is like Zen. See this?
>> PROBST: Checkerboard.
I like it. You seen enough?
Good? Vamanos?
>> Yeah, vamanos.
>> PROBST: Okay, good.
Thanks, guys.
>> Thank you.
>> All right.
>> AMBER: Muchas gracias.
>> Thank you, Raffa...
>> Welcome to Chez Saboga.
The first thing you see is our
gutter system, where our rain
collects, so all our bamboo that
turns up give us water down into
our pan. Right?
So the water... yeah.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
>> Esta tambien.
We have a little table, two beds
made.
All logs steady and sturdy.
He walked around, and everything
that was loose, he touched.
And I saw it in his face when we
walked down into the hut.
He didn't lie down.
Little footrest log.
I couldn't get it out of the
sand, so, it stays.
You could climb on this sucker.
Sturdy.
See, we want water to be able to
hit our bamboo, so there is
space in between the bamboo to
funnel down.
So, that way, we can get to our
water.
I'm trying like crazy to talk to
him.
He doesn't really have anything
to do with us.
And he's ready to go.
>> PROBST: If you receive a gift
from the sky and a clue to your
rice in your tree mail, it means
that Raffa thought you had the
best shelter.
If you receive only a clue in
your tree mail, it means he
thought you had the second best
shelter.
If you don't hear from us at
all, I hope it keeps you dry.
>> Thank you.
>> Thanks.
>> Thanks for coming.
>> Saboga?
Oh!
>> PROBST: You don't like...?
>> No, no, no.
>> PROBST: You would not want to
live here?
>> Oh, no way.
No.
>> He's shaking his head no.
>> This Saboga is very
dangerous.
>> PROBST: Dangerous?
>> Yeah, this is the
water, these are...
( whistles )... this.
( everyone talking at once )
>> And then I see him tell Jeff,
water go down in... bad.
>> I don't think he likes it.
>> I don't think he likes it,
either.
>> He doesn't.
>> PROBST: Our work is done.
Thank you.
Let's get out of here.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Raffa's made his
decision.
Make the drop of the
housewarming gift at...
( engine buzzing )
They're the winners.
>> Uh-oh.
>> It's a plane.
>> Oh, God, drop something, oh,
God, drop something.
Wait for...
Aw!
>> Come on, circle back.
>> It's all right.
Tomorrow's what really matters.
>> Sorry, guys.
It's totally my fault.
>> It's not your fault, Rupert.
>> Da plane! It's da plane!
Oh, God!
>> It's coming!
>> You know what?
>> Yeah, it's ours,
it's ours, it's ours!
Look! Dump it!
>> Yeah, here he comes.
( shouting )
>> Come on, now.
Come on, drop it.
>> Coming, coming, he's gonna
dump.
>> No way.
>> Yeah, it's ours, it's
ours, it's ours, look!
>> He's not over our beach, you
guys.
>> Yes, he is.
>> Yes, he is over our beach.
>> Yes, he is!
I think we got it.
>> And if we don't?
>> No, we don't. Yes, we do!
No...
>> Come on!
Right here! Drop it!
>> We're waiting for...
>> Oh, come on now.
( cheering )
>> Is that ours?
>> Is it ours, or is it theirs?
>> No, it's not.
( cheering )
>> It's theirs.
>> That's terrible.
That's such a bummer.
>> It better be a damn mansion.
It better have three stories.
( cheering )
>> We've never been so
excited in our lives.
That was just a pinnacle moment
for us since we've been here.
It was the happiest moment
ever... ever.
>> Oh, boy.
Oh, boy!
>> It's a mattress.
>> Oh, my God. Oh!
>> What's that, a tarp?
>> It's a tarp...
>> Oh, it's a tarp.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Pillows, pillows.
>> Blankets, oh, my God.
>> Wine!
( cheering )
Get that wine open.
Let's go.
You guys, we won first place.
>> Yeah.
>> Whoo!
>> All right?
>> Yeah, baby!
>> Give it up.
>> We wouldn't lose.
We haven't lost a thing yet.
The arm's up, so I'm assuming...
we have mail.
Yeah, baby.
Better be a clue.
I'm not waiting to open it.
Oh, it's a map.
And it's a clue, too.
Yeah, baby.
Clue two for rice.
That's so much more important
than anything else.
>> Drunk on day eight.
>> Oh, yeah, my chest is
all burning, and my stomach's
all burning...
>> Everything is all heavy.
>> Burning!
>> This is awesome.
>> I can't have too many
more of these sips.
>> Raffa never had so
much fun, going for a little
ride on the swing.
>> It was the swing...
>> Sue?
>> Hey, man, I don't drink.
>> She doesn't drink.
>> Not at all.
>> That's too bad.
>> More for you!
>> That could be the best
thing I've heard from Sue.
( all sighing )
>> Have you felt these pillows?
They're a little rough.
>> I'm getting drunker
and drunker...
>> Oh, give me the canteen.
The wine hit Amber a little bit
strong.
She wanted to start kissing
me in front of everybody.
>> If you're going to kiss
me, kiss me now, because I'm not
kissing you with nasty breath
later on.
Now I got wine breath.
>> Whoa!
Here's the thing.
Amber and I have been flirting
with each other since we got out
here.
We have an alliance together.
She probably thinks she's
playing me.
I probably think I'm playing
her.
Who knows how it's going to turn
out.
One thing's for sure though--
there can only be one winner in
this game.
( thunder crashing )
>> Oh, no.
Cue the thunder.
( thunder crashing )
>> Last night was an
absolute nightmare.
Just the queen mother of
all storms rolled through.
Our shelter was not really quite
prepared for that kind of storm,
and I can't imagine that any
shelter would be.
And you know, all of us kind of
dressed in our... well, all of
what we got, which is for must
of us just a pair of shorts and
a T-shirt or a tank top.
We were just...
I've never been so cold in my
life.
>> I'd get in the shelter.
You're in the rain.
So if I were you, I would sit up
there and, um...
I'm going to be under this.
Unless you want to stand here in
the rain.
What do you want to do?
>> I just want to let
you guys know that there's a lot
of things I thought I would be
able to overcome here-- just
missing family, missing home,
but my mom is really ill, and I
think I need to be with my
family.
I think family is the number one
thing right now.
And I think that they need me.
And as much as I don't want to
do it, it's a wise decision for
me to walk at this point in
time, so...
>> God, Jenna.
>> It frightens me that my mom--
something horrible might happen
to my mom while I'm here, and it
plagues me every day.
It follows me around like a dark
cloud.
And I don't think I'd ever
forgive myself if I knew that I
was here playing a game and
something happened to her.
>> Kathy, is she all right?
>> It's just too much for her.
Jenna was just a quivering,
shaking little leaf.
And she's finally collapsing.
Her mom is an a cancer rehab
home, and I didn't realize that.
She shouldn't be here actually,
in my opinion.
She should not be here.
And I just finally heard about
it.
She finally came up to me and
told me that, and I said, "You
know what, Jenna, you have every
right to be in the doldrums."
Every right.
>> Life is so short.
You blink and you're gone.
We're a tribe that has not
lost one challenge since
this game began.
And the reason for that is
because of output by all six
players.
Losing any one of those six
would be a detriment.
It would hurt a lot.
It would hurt morale, it would
hurt our performance.
You know, I don't even like to
think about the possibilities or
the what-if scenarios if Jenna
exits.
>> You're a good person.
And you won this sucker, man.
>> It's all good.
>> The thing is, you need
to know something, because this
is real.
It's becoming a bit of a cancer
eating away at us.
And so that's why, if you can
just hold that down to help us
out, because we need more
positive attitudes right now.
>> I completely agree with you.
>> We totally know what
you're going through, but let's
just wait to see what happens.
>> PROBST: Getting your first
look at the new Saboga tribe.
Rudy voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> Oh, my Rudy.
>> PROBST: He's gone, Richard.
First things first.
Give it up, Kathy.
Mariano.
Once again, immunity back up for
grabs.
So nine days in.
Starting to get into it now.
You guys have a lot of bug
bites.
How are you holding up, Jenna?
>> Bitten.
That's about the worst of it.
>> PROBST: Emotionally though,
all right?
>> Oh yeah,
emotionally we feel pretty good.
Plenty of water, plenty of food.
Shelter's working out pretty
good.
>> PROBST: How about you,
Chapera?
Amber, how you doing?
>> The bugs like me,
but it's all right.
>> PROBST: What's going on with
Mogo Mogo?
>> We got a couple of issues.
A couple of emotional things
going on.
>> PROBST: What's going on?
>> Okay.
( crying )
Wait.
Due to...
someone who's very ill
at home right now that's getting
worse, I need to pull myself out
of the game and be there.
I love this game so much, but my
priority is my family...
and it just doesn't make any
sense for me to be here anymore.
So I need to take myself out of
the game.
>> PROBST: So, are you talking
about your mom?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
She's just not any better and...
things have gotten a little
worse... quickly.
>> PROBST: You're talking as
though you're getting
information, updates on your
mom, in the last nine days.
>> No, it's just she's my
mother and I'm the only child.
I got a vibe.
I got a feeling that she needs
me there.
My dad needs me there.
Everybody needs me there.
I made a bad judgment call.
I shouldn't have came.
I thought that I could do it
and she would want me to and I,
I was wrong.
I should be there in case
something happens.
I'll never forgive myself.
You got to weigh out your
options.
I love this game, but it's, it's
my family.
>> PROBST: Alicia, what are you
thinking?
>> I think family's the
most important thing in the
world.
There's nothing you can ever put
above family.
I wouldn't have come out here to
begin with.
No matter whether my mother
said, "I want you to go," I
would have never came, ever.
>> Jenna admits her mistake.
Everybody makes it.
She admits her mistake.
>> But I wouldn't have,
I wouldn't have come.
>> PROBST: How about you, Amber?
>> ( crying )
I feel really bad for her.
Can I give her a hug?
>> PROBST: Of course.
>> Thank you.
>> I hope it works out.
>> This is the last thing
I wanted to do.
It really is.
I really wanted to play this
game, and I give all these
people more credit than ever,
'cause it's hard.
>> PROBST: So that's one of my
questions.
I just want to understand
exactly why you're leaving.
If you're leaving 'cause you
can't handle it...
>> No. I can handle it.
I handled it last time.
This is time I need with my
mother.
I need to be there sitting
by her bed, whether she's awake
or not.
I need to know that I had this
time with her while I could.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob.
>> Well, I don't think
it's right to even question her
motives.
We don't know what she's
thinking or how she's feeling.
I'm not one to get emotional,
and I know inside right now, I
feel butterflies.
So I say we just support her
decision and go from here.
>> PROBST: Rupert.
>> I feel bad for her,
but, you know...
to quit-- it's hard.
It's a hard decision.
>> Before I left, I told my
family, I made a commitment,
I was coming here, not staying
home.
If y'all got killed in a car
wreck, don't call me.
I'll be there after it's over,
but, now, I made that decision
for Big Tom.
And a lot of people are
different than Big Tom.
>> PROBST: You know, we all have
different values we place on
different things.
And I, I don't get the sense
that anybody here is saying,
"I'm right, she's wrong."
But you guys are being pretty
honest in saying, "Here's what I
would have done."
This is a big action with big
consequences.
And it could have a big impact
on this game.
We had an immunity challenge
that we don't need to run now.
Chapera, Saboga, you get off
easy, in a sense.
You get a free pass today.
Nothing at stake.
You're going back to camp.
Mogo Mogo, from a game point of
view, it hurts you.
This is a game about numbers.
You only have six to begin with.
You are now down to five.
That increases your chances of
being voted out at the next
Tribal Council.
We won't run the immunity
challenge.
We won't have an official Tribal
Council, but we do have the
formality of you going home.
Can you make it to Tribal
Council?
>> No.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I've pushed too far.
I don't think I can do it.
>> PROBST: Fair enough.
Let's bring in a boat.
Jenna.
We're thinking about you.
>> Thanks.
Bye, guys. Have fun.
>> ANNOUNCER: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor, Rob and
Amber heat things up.
>> You're so warm.
>> Boston Rob and Amber
are gonna do it.
>> ANNOUNCER: A storm wreaks
havoc.
>> It's not worth it.
>> ANNOUNCER: And a challenge
gets physical.
>> PROBST: Ethan throws it on
Colby.
>> Damn it!
>> When Jenna announced
that she was going home, there
was this mood that swung through
everybody and everybody's
shoulders went down and their
head hung low and it all brought
back the reality that it's
difficult out here, and even
though it's a game, there's a
whole lot more happening here.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
PARAMOUNT TELEVISION NETWORK