>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: A storm devastated
the Saboga Tribe.
>> The stupid shelter;
that I built was destroyed.
Digging into the sand
is the dumbest idea
I've ever had in my life.
>> PROBST: But at Chapera,
the tribe weathered the storm
in comfort...
>> I slept almost all
night long.
>> PROBST: ...giving Rob and
Amber's alliance a chance
to heat up.
>> You're so warm.
>> Boston Rob and Amber
are going to do it.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, Chapera continued
their winning streak.
Chapera... rice tonight.
In addition, take a shower,
get cleaned up.
Back at camp,
the tribe got clean
and found the final key
to their lockbox.
>> Oh.
>> You guys, that's alcohol.
That's whiskey.
>> Hey, guys, we got rice!
>> PROBST: The rice helped
Chapera to an early lead
during a very physical
immunity challenge.
Chapera, first to start
building the puzzle.
But the puzzle proved difficult,
and Saboga and Mogo Mogo
both took immunity,
leaving Chapera
with their first immunity loss.
Before Tribal Council,
the two Robs made a pact.
>> We can make good allies.
>> I agree.
>> I made an alliance with
Boston Rob, and a deal's a deal.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Rob C. learned
he'd been played.
Rob, the tribe has spoken.
Fourteen are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(birds chirping)
>> Uno, dos, tres, cuatro.
>> ♪ Well, last time I seen
her standing on a hill ♪
Shaking her boobs and... ♪
( all yelling and singing )
>> We got to build a boat!
>> Oh, my God.
>> I did this in Marquesas.
>> "Put on your game face
for this reward
you will compete.
This may change your situation
and the quantities you eat.
Here are the supplies
to build a raft,
one that four of you can race.
Tribe pride is on the line.
You'd better keep up the pace."
>> Four of us can race.
Chances are, Tom, you might
sit out, 'cause you're
the biggest guy.
You're going to drag
the boat down, so...
>> I'm an anchor.
>> Well, this morning we got
some tree mail which
involves building a raft.
We got a bunch of bamboo,
some rope and one paddle.
The biggest part of the
challenge is obviously
building it.
>> We'll probably be... here...
to have the two power strokes.
You'll be there.
You put two bundles and then
the platform right on it.
Then we're making outriggers.
It's like a big catamaran.
>> Apparently, we're building
a pontoon boat, a catamaran
possibly-- I'm not sure--
with two bundles of bamboo
underneath supporting the
platform.
It sounds great in theory.
I hope it works.
I'm a little bit worried
about building stuff now,
ever since our...
first shelter fiasco.
>> I love it.
>> Let's start lashing the top
to it.
I feel very good about the raft.
I'm trying to not think
about the house.
You know, I got my reputation
riding on this damn thing again.
>> Okay, guys, we have
to win this today.
We're going to have to paddle
our asses off.
>> We came up with a good
design, and with four paddles,
we should be able to fly.
We want to win.
>> The key is you got to use
every blooming piece of bamboo.
>> Do you use full length,
or do you make it shorter?
>> Full length.
>> Yeah?
>> Why?
>> 'Cause, you know what?
It's too much energy
to cut it down.
>> It could be very,
very, very simple.
These bundles, as they are,
will never sink.
Don't think too hard.
Simple is always better.
The challenge was
to construct a raft...
that was worthy...
of the sea
and could carry four of us.
So that meant this raft
not only had to carry Lex
and Kathy and I
and a normal human being,
but it's got to carry
260 pounds of Hatch.
>> I think it's good for
steering.
>> Let's kind of go back and
forth and see how stable it is.
But ultimately,
it came down to laziness
and pure exhaustion
that designed that raft,
and nothing more.
>> The raft will definitely
float, but it won't be swift.
It will not be swift.
>> I'm going to tell
you something.
That raft...
That one's going to
win us this challenge.
>> I say nice rack...
Oh, raft.
>> Yeah, wait.
Have you been drinking?
>> No. No, I just...
I-I meant "raft"
when I said "rack."
>> Hey, Tom, I got
your waterbed for you.
>> All right.
>> That's the best built thing
since Alicia.
>> If I could vote anybody out
right now, it'd be Tom.
He's a stupid drunk.
A stupid klutzy drunk.
I don't care for the man
whatsoever.
I don't think his sexual
innuendoes are funny.
>> I christen the ship.
>> Tom came down with the
whiskey to christen the vessel.
>> I christen...
>> Oh, yeah!
>> And I'm like, "Oh, you guys,
don't move, I got to pee."
So I peed right on the raft.
So that we decided that I
christened it right there.
>> You pissed on it?
It's supposed to be
pure grain liquor.
Kiss my ass.
What a hag.
My God, that's going to make
a hole in the driftwood.
That'll rot any wood I know.
I'm afraid the ship's
going to sink now.
Where did Sue piss?
>> Right here.
>> Go, Tom, you do the honors.
>> Okay.
>> I christen thee...
>> I christen thee vessel
the Suzie Q., in honor
of me old lady Sue.
( all cheer )
And in the honor,
I shall take one little goober.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
What's going on, Saboga?
>> Life's good.
>> PROBST: What's up, Mogo Mogo?
Come on in, Chapera.
Getting your first look at the
new Chapera tribe.
>> Damn, Sue's still here.
>> Cesternino.
>> PROBST: Rob voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
Nobody's safe in this game.
All right, you ready
for today's challenge?
>> Yes, sir.
This morning,
you were given materials,
told to build a raft.
Here's how the challenge works:
two tribe members
will start on the raft.
Their job, paddle out and rescue
two other tribe members
who have been stranded
in the water
on separate floating platforms.
Once you've picked up
both tribe members,
continue out to a buoy.
You'll grab a flag,
paddle back to shore
up the beach,
across the finish line.
First two tribes to get back
with their boat and run
across the finish line
with their flag win reward.
Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For the winning
tribe...
What might be in here,
Hatch?
>> Fish hooks.
>> PROBST: Fishing hooks.
To go along with the fishing
hooks, a fishing spear.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: Should make fishing
a whole lot easier.
In addition, for the
first two tribes,
a clue to your lock box.
Chapera, it has no value to you.
You've already had your rice
and most of your whiskey...
but for Saboga
and Mogo Mogo, it could
mean rice tonight.
For the third part of the
reward, the tribe that
finishes last will be dissolved.
>> What?
>> PROBST: The tribe members
will be absorbed
by the two remaining tribes.
We're going to have
a school yard game
of "Pick 'Em."
We will alternate picks.
The winning tribe
gets to pick first.
For the losing tribe,
you will not return
back to your beach.
Your personal items and any
other clothing items will be
sent to your new home.
Everything else: rewards,
your shelter, tools, anything
else you've acquired,
you'll never see again.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Chapera, you have
one extra member.
Who sat out during
the building of the raft?
>> Big Tom.
>> PROBST: So you won't
participate in this.
Mogo Mogo, who sat out?
>> Shii Ann.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann.
So you won't participate either.
I'll give you a couple
of minutes to strategize.
Wait for my go.
Here we go, guys:
a reward challenge
with huge stakes.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, Mogo Mogo!
>> PROBST: Everybody even
off the start.
All rafts are floating.
That's a good sign.
>> We got it.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo out
to a slight lead.
Saboga's raft looks nice,
but it's slow.
Mogo Mogo pulling away
with the worst-looking raft
of the three.
Mogo Mogo approaches Kathy.
Don't jump in, Kathy.
Get on.
Mogo Mogo still
with the big lead.
Saboga approaches
their first member,
looking to pick up Jenna.
Chapera close to picking up
Alicia.
Alicia pulls 'em in
tight and steps onboard.
Chapera has their
first tribe member.
Saboga has their
Mogo Mogo increases their lead.
Lex, Colby and Kathy
nearing Richard.
Richard pulls 'em close.
Hatch is onboard.
( indistinct talking )
>> PROBST: Saboga by far
with the best looking raft
and the least effective.
Chapera nears Amber.
Amber's onboard.
Chapera has all their tribe
members, heading for the flag.
Mogo Mogo at their flag.
Kathy reaches for the flag...
and she has it.
Mogo Mogo heading back.
Saboga has all
four tribe members.
They're heading for their flag.
Chapera making up some ground.
( indistinct shouting )
Chapera reaches for
their tribe flag.
They have it-- Chapera
has their flag.
They're heading back.
Mogo Mogo with a big lead.
>> Come on, Mogo Mogo.
>> PROBST: Saboga needs to make
up a lot of ground.
Losing tribe will be dissolved,
absorbed by the other two
tribes.
You do not want to be last
in this challenge.
Rupert has the flag for Saboga.
It is a race back to shore
between Saboga and Chapera
for second place.
( shouts of encouragement )
>> PROBST: Hit the flag with
your raft and you're there.
>> Hit it! Hit it!
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo's clear.
It's a race in to the finish.
Mogo Mogo celebrating
before they even finish.
>> Come on,
run to the finish line!
( shouts of joy )
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo wins reward
and keeps their tribe together.
Let's go, Saboga!
Let's go, Chapera!
>> We get to pick first. Okay.
Bring him along, Rich.
>> Yeah, bring him along.
>> Bring him?
>> It's coming.
It's coming.
>> PROBST: Chapera, raft's got
to hit the flag.
You're clear.
It's a race across
the finish line.
Chapera finishes second,
keeps their tribe intact.
( applause )
Saboga finishes last, and Saboga
will soon be no longer.
>> PROBST: Okay, first things
first.
Mogo Mogo.
Your fishing spear.
>> Yes!
Richard!
>> PROBST: Hooks.
( whoops )
>> PROBST: Last clue to the lock
box.
Find the key, you'll have rice.
Here's how it's going to work:
it is a schoolyard pick 'em.
Mogo Mogo, since you won,
you'll pick first.
As you are selected, come to me,
we'll trade buffs.
Mogo Mogo, who's your first
pick?
>> Ethan.
>> PROBST: Ethan, come on over.
Saboga no more.
Mogo Mogo.
Chapera, first pick?
>> Rupert.
>> PROBST: Rupert, no longer
a member of Saboga.
You are now a member of Chapera.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo, make your
next pick.
>> Jerri.
>> Come on, Jerri.
>> PROBST: Jerri and Colby
reunited.
Jerri now a member of Mogo Mogo.
Jenna, you get the honor, if
it is, putting Saboga to rest.
You're now a member of Chapera.
( cheering )
All right, guys,
you all have a lot of time
to get to know each other--
head back to camp.
>> All right, guys, on three.
Ready?
One, two, three...
>> Mogo Mogo!
>> Welcome home, you guys.
>> I'm... so happy.
>> Winning the Reward Challenge,
the biggest reward
was gaining control
of dismantling Saboga.
We chose Ethan because we knew
if we had him on our tribe,
we had control of how long
he stays in this game.
And then after that,
we just wanted someone
that we didn't think
he had bonded with that much,
and Jerri was the answer.
We still have
the original Mogo Mogo Tribe,
and Jerri and Ethan are
on the outside looking in.
>> Oh, my God!
This is beautiful.
>> And see our little balcony?
>> I love it.
>> Wow, that's fantastic.
>> It's pretty waterproof.
>> You guys, this is amazing.
>> I feel like
my entire time out here,
every day I've started over.
And now I'm on a new tribe,
start over again.
It's just, like, one big...
first day for me.
>> Can I just say thank you.
I'm very, very happy
to be over here.
>> Good!
We're happy you're here.
>> I'm gonna cry.
>> We're glad to have you.
>> I swore I wouldn't
cry anymore.
My spirits are
very high right now.
I don't miss Saboga at all.
Not even a little.
>> You'll be happy.
You'll be happy here.
>> I will be very happy here.
>> I can't believe
it worked out like that,
I can't believe it.
Wait till you see our camp.
>> Over at Saboga,
I had complete control,
and I was telling everyone
who to vote off.
And then they dissolved us,
which I don't like,
because the first 13 days
that I had put into this game
washed down the toilet.
>> Oh, man.
>> Cool, right?
( Rupert laughing )
>> Sit down.
>> Oh, my God.
>> We have the swing set
and the chess board.
>> Does it hold you, Tom?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I can sit? Oh, my God.
>> Their camp is...
( exhales )
...compared to our camp,
our camp was hobo junction.
Theirs is the Taj Mahal.
( indistinct chatter )
>> We're home! We're home!
Yay!
>> We're going to kick
the green team's ass.
( applause )
>> It's in a shallow grave.
>> First thing this morning,
got up, went and looked for
the key.
( key rattling )
( cheering )
>> It felt so good to find it.
I was so excited.
Everybody's, like, "Yay, Jerri!"
I'm feeling, "Yay,
now I'm a part of Mogo Mogo."
>> Oh, nice.
( gasps )
>> Oh, my God.
Wow.
>> Wow. Oh, nice.
>> The rice is soggy.
>> Oh, my God, it's totally wet.
Unfortunately, when we opened
the carton, the rice...
half the rice was rotten.
>> We lost a lot of rice.
The note on the box did say,
"Keep this dry. Very valuable."
And we tried our best.
I've run out of rice
once before, and the
consequences aren't good.
I don't want to do it again.
Even though we have rice,
we do still need fish.
I'm going to go when it gets
low, so that's probably
hour and a half.
I'm not going to go till then.
If you have any interest
in high tide...
>> I'm gonna try it
for a little bit, too.
>> Go get 'em, man.
>> Good luck, Ethan.
>> I think Ethan's always,
uh, playing the game--
he's, "Sure, I'll go try,
sure I'll go try," not wanting
to go step on my toes.
"No. Are you going to go?
No? If you're not,
I'll go try when you aren't."
Ooh, he's good.
>> Ethan, how'd you do?
>> Not much, but...
every little bit helps.
I went out there
and I went spear fishing.
Inside I'm jumping, I'm like,
"I caught my first fish!"
And I see Richard's face,
he's, like, competition.
Like, I felt scared.
I didn't want to, you know,
step on his toes.
>> You got a trigger.
Killer.
>> Hot dog.
>> He got a fish.
I'm the only one
that's supposed to get fish.
I'm gonna have to fix that up
and bring back 12 now.
>> Oh, my God, look at the fish
that you've got.
>> Two of them.
>> It's huge.
( cheering )
>> All right, Richard!
>> Guys want to feud
on how many fish they bring in,
( laughs ): rock on.
We'll just have lots of fish,
'cause the boys are just playing
one-up on each other.
>> We have a ton of fish here.
Oh, Richard, that looks awesome.
>> "Two new tribes, now we'll
see whose speed and strength
earn immunity.
It's really quite simple.
Capture the flag, that's it.
Winners end up with the idol.
Losers end up in the pit."
>> I think we'll win,
and if we don't, who cares?
There's a lot of people
we got to get rid of.
Nobody heard me say that.
>> That sounds great.
>> That's fun, I mean...
>> Yeah, this is gonna be fun.
>> Thus far, our mantra has
been, "slow and steady wins the
race."
It's served us well.
We came in second place.
Second place now sends you home.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
First things first.
Lex, I will take one half of
the immunity idol, put it with
the other half that I
retrieved from Saboga,
which is no more.
We now have one idol.
One winner, one loser.
All right, for today's Immunity
Challenge, both tribes
must navigate their way
along a series
of narrow balance beams
to retrieve tribe-colored flags
from the opposite end
of the course.
In the middle is a battle
bridge.
When two opposing tribe members
meet on opposite ends
of the bridge, it is
a physical showdown.
Your goal, get the other tribe
member off that bridge
and into the water.
The first person to hit the
water returns to the start,
forfeits their flag.
Winner moves on.
A tribe can only have
two members on the course
at any time.
You got to retain
a revolving order.
The first tribe to get 20 flags
from one side to the other
wins immunity,
guaranteed a one-in-13 shot
at a million dollars.
Take a spot on your platform,
wait for my go.
Here we go.
For immunity...
survivors ready?
Go!
>> Let's go, Hatch.
>> PROBST: Big Tom and Hatch
on the course.
Shii Ann, Amber on the course.
Hatch having a little trouble,
causing a roadblock.
>> Good job.
>> Go, Tom.
Take your time, Tom.
>> PROBST: Amber, Amber,
Amber, Amber, look at that.
Nice!
>> Close, Amber.
>> Come on there, Amber.
>> Nice, Shii Ann,
very nice.
>> Nice job, guys.
>> Nice job, Hatch.
>> PROBST: Hatch has a flag.
He's got to get back.
>> Come on, Tommy.
>> Go get him, Tom.
( yells )
>> PROBST: Hatch is down.
Drop the flag,
and go to the start.
>> Take your time, take your
time, Tom, relax.
Take your time, Tom.
>> Come on, Tom, get across,
get across now.
>> Go all the way across, Tom.
Come on! Tom, bring the flag.
>> Bring the flag.
>> PROBST: Big Tom wanted a
showdown, Ethan not interested.
>> All the way across, Tom.
Come on, Tom...
>> Oh, Shii Ann takes
a dip in the water.
Drop the flag,
head back to the start.
>> You can do it.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Big Tom with a flag.
>> Come on, Amber, good job.
>> PROBST: Amber with a flag.
Chapera up 2-0.
Boston Rob waiting
for a showdown.
He has planted it
at the battle bridge.
We have our first showdown.
Here's how it's going to work.
You'll both come out
into the middle of the bridge.
I'm going to say,
"Three, two, one, go."
On "go," you go.
Three, two, one, go.
( shouting )
>> Go, Ethan!
Let's go, Ethan!
Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: The first one to hit
the water's out.
Boston Rob hit the water first.
Ethan took a big header
on the side of the pool.
>> Ethan, are you okay?
>> PROBST: You all right?
>> Good job, Easy.
>> PROBST: Ethan, you hop up
here on the platform.
Boston Rob's back at the start.
Rupert, back to the start.
Balance, a very big part
of this challenge.
>> All right, Ethan.
>> Ethan with the first flag
for Mogo Mogo.
It's Chapera two, Mogo Mogo one.
( indistinct voices )
>> PROBST: Jerri with another
flag for Mogo Mogo.
>> Yeah, yeah...
>> PROBST: Hatch and Jenna in a
battle.
>> Oh, baby girl.
>> Have you ever heard the story
of David and Goliath?
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
>> Beat him, Jenna.
Come on, Jenna.
Go for his feet.
Don't let him get you.
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Jenna hits the water
first.
Jenna's out.
>> No way! He hit the water...
>> No!
>> Yeah!
>> Come on, Hatch.
>> Oh, come on.
>> Nice job, girls.
>> Nice job, Hatch.
>> PROBST: Kathy with another
flag for Mogo Mogo.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Alicia with another
flag for Chapera.
We're tied up 3-3.
>> Go easy, Tom. Go easy.
>> PROBST: Big Tom...
Oh, oh!
>> He's still up!
Get up there, Tommy! Yeah!
>> PROBST: Still on the course.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Wow!
That's going to hurt tomorrow.
>> There she is, Tommy!
>> PROBST: Hold up, guys.
We have a battle.
Big Tom and Ethan.
Come on, Ethan.
Three, two, one, go.
( shouting )
>> Tom won!
>> PROBST: Ethan, first in the
water.
Big Tom moving on.
>> Come on, Sue. Nicely done.
>> You got it, Kathy.
>> Sue, get up there.
>> I want this one.
I got to take my time.
Move, baby!
( speaks indistinctly )
>> Excuse me.
>> Want some?
>> Good job. Yeah, right.
>> Want some, honey?
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Guys, come on.
Nobody cares about that stuff.
>> Yeah, we don't, Richard.
>> Come on, Alicia.
You're doing great now.
Just cruise it.
Cruise it, Alicia, cruise it.
>> Colby, get to the beam,
quick.
>> PROBST: We have a showdown.
West Coast versus East Coast.
Colby versus Boston Rob.
Three, two, one, go.
>> Come on, Rob. Go, Rob!
Win it!
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Colby hits the water
first, Boston Rob moves on.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: We're going.
>> Nice, Rupert.
>> Good job!
>> Nice, Rupert!
( grunting )
>> PROBST: Rupert still unable
to make it across.
Head back to the start.
Boston Rob is out of control.
He has a flag,
and he's heading back.
>> Come on, Rob.
>> Take your time, Rob.
Take your time.
>> Careful, Rob,
we need those flags.
Boston Rob, no trouble.
>> Be careful.
>> I'm jumping off,
so Rob can go on.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann in with
another flag for Mogo Mogo.
Rob in with the 18th flag.
Strategy coming into play.
Most of the Chapera tribe
falling off,
so Rob can run the course.
Boston Rob going
for Chapera's final leg.
>> Come on, you got it,
bring it home!
Mogo Mogo going to have
to engage in battle,
or Chapera's going to walk away
with this.
>> Come on, Rob.
Boston Rob versus Kathy.
>> Go low, go low!
Three, two, one, go.
Kathy, good strategy.
>> Rob, you got to do
the same thing.
>> Do the same thing,
Rob, get down.
>> Come on, Rob.
Nice!
>> There we go!
>> PROBST: Kathy hits the water.
Let him go.
>> Jump again. Jump.
>> Amber heading in.
>> No! No! No! No! No! No!
>> PROBST: That's 19 for
Chapera.
Boston Rob has the winning flag.
Go!
Chapera wins immunity.
( cheering )
>> You did it!
>> Good strategy.
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Chapera, immunity.
Safe from Tribal Council.
( cheering )
Mogo Mogo,
Tribal Council tonight.
Won't be the first time
you've lost a member.
It will be the first time
you're voting out a member.
You have this afternoon to think
about who that's going to be.
I'll see you there.
Head on back.
>> Those guys were freaking out.
Did you hear Richard?
He whined.
>> Yeah, they were like,
"They're jumping,
they're jumping.
Everybody's jumping!"
>> "Look, they're all
just jumping off."
>> You call it what you want to,
we call it winning.
>> Yeah, hell, yeah.
Some of us got no balance.
>> I hope they vote Richard off,
'cause what he did to
me was absolutely...
>> That was disgusting.
( all talking )
>> I wanted to get past,
so I wouldn't have to
battle Richard naked.
It felt real good to be able
to propel my team to the win.
And I may not be
as strong as some of them,
but I guarantee I'm tougher
than every single one of them.
>> Welcome to reality.
And you got Colby in.
( shouting )
>> You got him.
>> Colby?
Yeah, he's not as tough
as you think, ladies.
>> Chapera!
( cheering )
>> We lost the challenge, and,
uh, it was... it was a blow.
I really like our tribe, and now
we have to go to Tribal.
So... the game is on.
For the first time at Mogo
Mogo, the game is really on.
>> Oh, it's a downer.
But I also don't like
sitting around the camp
talking about
would have, could have,
should have.
You know, it's time
to move on.
>> Yeah.
>> This is a game where
the more you strategize
and the more
you think about it,
the more you change your mind.
Because a lot of times,
your gut will tell you
something totally different
than what you've
already agreed to do.
So, basically
here's where we are--
Richard's the one
we got to get rid of.
He's the snake in the grass...
>> I agree.
>> ...that's gonna cause us
the most trouble.
He's just... he's a cancer
in this tribe, and he's going.
If you give Richard time enough,
he will fester and then
he will spread, you know?
>> But do you think
he's strong enough to keep
around for more challenges?
>> No. No.
We can do without him.
Um... the cool thing is,
he thinks we're dropping
you tonight, so, we're just
going to let him think that,
okay?
>> The plan tonight is
to vote off Richard Hatch.
For all I know, they're going
to vote me off.
You know, I'm super paranoid,
but, um...
I think I got a 50-50 shot.
>> Okay?
>> All right.
>> I was approached by...
Lex, Colby and Ethan
to vote for Rich.
I immediately said,
"Hell, yeah, count me in."
But the downside is,
it doesn't make any sense
for me to team up with
three guys who are then going
to kick my ass
in every challenge afterwards.
>> He just took off to go...
>> Get clams.
>> Clamming, yeah.
>> What's his thought?
>> Well, I said, "I can't tell
you "you're going home tonight,
but I can't tell you
you're not, either."
You know, you showed
in those challenges
how dominant you are
as a swimmer and runner
and everything else.
There's no question nobody wants
to compete with you.
>> Right.
>> So I guess I got
to go with you, I
got to believe you.
I got to believe you're with me,
'cause Ethan would be more
of a physical threat
to you.
>> When Ethan and Jerri
joined our tribe,
we all agreed that Ethan
would be the first to go.
Now all of a sudden,
Lex is coming up to me and Kathy
and telling us it's Richard.
Richard. Richard Hatch.
It's a mistake.
I think... it's a mistake.
If we take Richard out now,
who do we have?
Just you and me.
>> Well, we got to think
about it some more.
I need to think before I react.
We got to think more.
>> What do you think
about all this craziness
that's going on?
>> I know.
>> I mean, if we vote
Colby, I'm in.
>> I know you are.
>> I'm trying to convince Kathy
that instead of Rich, it's
Colby.
My own personal reasons.
Some revenge involved, for sure.
I got screwed over by
Colby once already.
>> I totally see it.
>> I mean, worse than you
could ever imagine,
and I would hate to put
myself in a position
to repeat the same mistake.
>> The only thing that
bothered me today
with this decision,
it wasn't unilateral.
You know, Colby didn't come
to all of us.
He just went up there
and made that decision.
>> Yeah, and that's
exactly what I mean.
>> I don't know,
it's a hard call.
It's a big move.
>> Okay, if you start
thinking differently,
just let me know.
>> I will.
>> I'm on your side.
>> Okay, same here.
( laughs )
>> I don't want to fall prey
to the same person who
screwed me over in Australia.
>> Time for a Tribal Council,
and everything starts
going haywire-- it's great.
>> See, everything's flushing
out right now.
>> Now Jerri says she's been
approached to get rid of me.
The only way that could possibly
have happened
is Ethan, Lex and Colby.
>> I think, if we go in,
we vote for Colby, I'm in.
I'm in 100%.
>> Okay, that's it, then.
'Cause if you're not
for anything else,
then we'll just do that.
All right, Colby goes.
So they blew it.
How dare you approach somebody
to get rid of me?
You must go bye-bye now.
So Colby has to go home.
( thunder crashing )
>> Well, Ethan and Lex and Colby
feel like they're the strongest
and will hold the
challenges together.
So what do you say-- Colby?
You don't know yet?
You're going to let me
know when you decide.
>> I know.
Give me ten minutes.
>> All right.
( chuckles )
( mimics giggling )
>> Colby and Richard are
on the chopping block tonight,
and I have got myself
in the middle.
I don't know how I got there.
So do you trust your gut?
Do you trust loyalty?
Or do you just go with
sort of what makes sense?
And where am I going?
I don't know.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Tribal
Council.
This is the first time
the original Mogo Mogo
has had to deal with the task
of voting somebody out.
Before we get to that,
let's talk a little bit.
Going back to the
Reward Challenge,
Richard, that raft
didn't look like
it was going to make it
three feet in the water.
>> Come on, you knew we were
going to win as soon as you saw
that bundle of joy.
>> PROBST: That was Bad News
Bears for sure.
As a result, you get
two new tribe members.
Ethan, you were the first person
picked in the school yard "Pick
'Em. "
Was your initial instinct,
"Hey, they like me,"
or "Wow, I'm in trouble"?
>> A little bit of both.
But as you know, you remember
that first Tribal Council,
my back was against the wall,
so I was just happy
to have a change of pace
and, you know, just get
a new lease on life, really.
>> PROBST: Colby, how are you
doing second time around?
>> I mean, it is
a much different experience
because everyone
knows how to play this game,
and so you cannot coast, uh,
although a lot of people
are doing it.
>> PROBST: Kathy,
how much more difficult is it
playing with 18 people
who are really good
at this game?
>> Oh, it's 100% the other
direction than when we were
playing before.
There was loyalty the last time,
you know, where you'd get
friendships and bondings.
And, uh, right now
it's just pure unadulterated
playing the game.
>> PROBST: Hatch, how busy was
the afternoon back at camp,
because it's game on now.
For the first time,
you have to vote somebody out.
>> Yeah, it's true.
This is our first time
somebody's got to go.
Of course, you know,
I have no target on my back.
( blows air thorough lips )
( Richard chuckles )
>> PROBST: Colby, what
went on at camp this afternoon
when you got back?
It had to be a busy
afternoon, positioning.
>> It was. Yeah, it was.
It was.
It's a hard day when
you got to go back,
and you have a few
hours to scramble.
Ultimately,
someone's getting duped.
Someone is having the wool
pulled over their eyes, and...
( chuckles )
you won't know until that vote
goes up whether it's you.
>> PROBST: What are you basing
your vote on tonight?
>> Um, cutting out the cancer.
>> PROBST: How about for you,
Kathy?
>> Taking the big players
out--taking the power players
out.
>> PROBST: Surprised who you're
voting for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: And with that,
it's time to vote.
Ethan, you're up.
>> It does come down to this.
You really could have trusted
me.
I was... I was on your side.
I know that's hard to believe,
but it's true.
>> Hatch, you're a hell of
a player and you almost had me
convinced I can trust you.
But my gut told me not to.
I'm not going to.
Best of luck.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave the
Tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Colby.
Hatch.
Rich.
Two votes: Rich.
One vote: Colby.
Hatch.
That's three votes: Rich.
One vote: Colby.
The fifth person voted out
of Survivor: All-Stars...
Rich.
>> I've been bamboozled!
>> PROBST: That's four.
That's enough.
>> Good on you all.
Man, oh, man.
>> We played it, didn't we?
>> ( chuckles ): Yeah, you did.
>> PROBST: Rich, the tribe
has spoken.
>> Food. Food.
>> PROBST: Well, if tonight's
vote showed you one thing,
it ought to be this:
when you are competing
against players
of this caliber in this game,
it doesn't matter
how good you are,
you are always at risk.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
My strategy was pointed out
by Colby last night.
Someone like you doesn't have
to lie this entire game because
you don't make a decision.
I don't have
any respect for that.
>> Captain America with his
good teeth, blah, blah, blah.
>> PROBST: And Sue speaks out.
It wasn't "sort of," Jeff!
I was humiliated and totally
spent, Jeff!
>> Oops!
( laughs )
So much for what I thought.
I'm gone.
How much fun is Survivor?
Yeah, I was blown out
of the water today
and didn't even know it.
I've never had my torch snuffed.
I've never had it put out,
and here I am, I'm gone.
I'm gone.
Oh, fifth out of the game.
I wanted the check again.
Damn.