>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
With Lex voted out, Kathy was
feeling the pain of being
betrayed by Rob.
>> I couldn't believe how
isolated I felt.
It's really hard being on the
losing side of life here.
>> PROBST: And the tribe faced
a monumental competition.
Today's challenge is a Survivor
obstacle course, one of the
toughest we've ever had.
It is part reward and it is part
immunity.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Divided into two
teams, Rob's team dominated the
competition, winning ponchos and
letters from home and advancing
them to the immunity portion of
the challenge.
Go.
Once again, Rob sealed his
victory.
Boston Rob wins immunity and a
video of his brother.
But Rob surprised his tribe
mates with an interesting
proposition.
>> We had some bad blood
yesterday.
Is there any way, if I forego
seeing the video, everybody
could get their letters?
>> PROBST: I can make that
trade.
With Tribal Council looming,
Kathy and Shii Ann tried to stir
things up in an attempt to save
themselves.
>> You need to start reacting.
>> I think we've got some
last-minute scrambling going on
in Panama today.
>> PROBST: But for Kathy, all
the talk just wasn't enough.
She was voted out and became
the second member of the jury.
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
( thunder crashing )
>> Well, last night was really
emotional.
Um, I got really choked up when
they voted Kathy out.
The smug, horrible Chaperan...
superior tribe pagonging all of
us Mogo Mogo members, you know,
basically voting one after
another out.
I knew Kathy was going, and I
just got really emotional
because she was my rock out
here.
And she was my one true friend.
And now that she's gone, I don't
have anyone here.
I've got no one.
( thunder rolling )
I know I'm slated next to go.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And you know I have to play
the game as hard as I can
before I go.
So, I'm just asking you
straight-up, you know, are you
going to keep with your original
six, or are you going to be
willing to look at other
possibilities?
>> Yeah...
Like, honestly, I'm going to
stay with my plan.
>> That's cool.
You got to play your last card.
>> Win immunity.
>> I'm going to try
to win immunity. I will.
>> You've got to beat me,
though, 'cause I need it just as
much as you.
I know I do, you know?
>> I know you do.
I'm extremely vulnerable right
now, and chances of me making it
to the final two are slim.
So, at this point, my best
chance is to play as hard as I
can, call everyone on their game
and stir it up before I leave.
If you make it to the final two,
I'll be shocked.
>> I know.
>> With your strategy...
current strategy.
And I hope you do well, but, you
know, I'm wishing myself luck in
the next immunity challenge.
>> She tried to tell me
what my strategy should be.
>> Right.
>> "You need to watch out
for this person, you need to
watch out for this one."
>> Here we go.
>> She's doing that.
Just was patient and listened
to her.
I was like, "All right, thanks
for the info, Shii Ann."
We got to make sure she don't
win immunity.
>> Hell, yeah.
That's the whole goal.
>> That's it.
( thunderclap )
( twittering )
>> Can it rain any more here?
Look, there's a bump on it.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Wow, it's a mask.
>> It says, "A no-lose
situation, this one's not
a race.
Is everyone a winner?
Try not the lose face.
In touch with your own feelings?
What do your tribe mates think?
If you're the last one standing,
you'll decide what they eat
and drink."
>> Oh...
>> So maybe you get to choose
whether or not you want share...
>> So maybe you choose what
everybody eats?
>> I want...
>> I want everybody to eat
and drink.
>> The rain doesn't let up.
We can't fish in these
conditions.
We can't cook in these
So, we are all hoping we're
playing for food.
>> "Try not to lose face" is
maybe three chops and your face
is smashed and you're out.
>> I'm hoping food or something,
but I'm really looking forward
to it because it's just a
miserable day.
Ooga, ga, ga, ooga, go, ga.
Hey-a, ho-a, ha.
>> Dumb ass.
( thunderclap )
>> PROBST: Rain ponchos coming
in handy.
( Rupert chuckling )
>> PROBST: Seeing your likeness?
>> Yeah.
Amber and I are the same person,
just slightly different hair.
>> Look at me.
>> I have a very strange
expression on our faces.
( men chuckling )
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the first part of today's
reward challenge.
I'm gonna hand each of you a
questionnaire about your fellow
tribe mates.
The idea here is to find out
what you really think about each
other.
So, answer honestly.
Don't discuss your answers with
anybody.
Make sense?
All right, give you a couple
minutes to do this.
Find a little spot, step away
from each other.
All right, guys.
The results have been tallied.
I'm going to ask you the same
exact questions again, only this
time your answers should be
based on how you think the
majority of the tribe answered.
Every time your answer matches
what the tribe said, you get to
make one chop on a tribe
mate's row.
Three chops release a battering
ram and you're out of the game.
Last person left standing wins
reward.
The reward is food.
However, all of you will be
picked up by boat and taken to a
local Panamanian restaurant.
On the menu are seven items.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Each item increases
in value and taste, everything
from a bowl of rice and a glass
of water from your own camp to a
full-on steak dinner with all
the fixings.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: The winner will be in
charge of that menu.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Here's the rub: You
cannot share your meal.
Somebody will get a whole lot,
and somebody is gonna get
very little.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: All right.
Let's get started.
First question: Who would you
trust with your life?
Everybody reveal.
The group thought Rob.
Alicia got it right.
Amber got it right.
Rob, you didn't even get it
right.
Alicia, you get the first chop.
>> Oh, Shii Ann, Shii Ann.
>> Surprise.
>> PROBST: Amber, you're up.
Who's getting the damage?
>> I'm going to go for Big Tom
since he stole my pot in that
one challenge.
>> PROBST: Now we're going to
get catty.
Who does not deserve to be an
all-star?
Not an easy question to
answer... in front of each
other.
Reveal.
It was a tie.
Shii Ann.
>> Surprise.
>> PROBST: Alicia.
>> Nice.
Hearing that from the rest of
the tribe, what's that make
you feel?
>> Yeah, it's a shot in the
heart.
I'll get them all later.
>> PROBST: Well, everybody got
it right.
Everybody gets a chop.
We'll start on the end and
work down.
>> Well, since my own tribe
mates think I don't deserve
to be here, Rob...
you're going first.
>> PROBST: Rob takes a hit.
>> How do you like that, baby?
>> PROBST: Jenna?
>> I'm going to go with Big Tom.
>> PROBST: Big Tom takes his
second hit.
One hit away from being out of
the game.
Shii Ann.
>> Hey, Alicia, I got to pay
you back.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Amber.
>> I'll go with Jenna.
>> PROBST: Jenna takes her
first hit.
Rupert.
>> I'm sorry, Shii Ann.
Shii Ann and Big Tom one hit
away from being out of the game.
Big Tom.
>> Jenna, I'll just pay you
a favor.
Right back to you, baby.
>> PROBST: Jenna takes her
second hit.
Boston Rob, you could put
somebody out of the game if you
wanted.
>> Rupert hasn't gotten hit yet.
>> Oh...
( all groaning )
>> PROBST: Big Tom is our first
casualty!
>> That's rotten.
>> PROBST: Have a seat on the
bench, Big Tom.
You're out of the game.
Next question: "Who uses sex
appeal as a weapon?"
Nobody even hesitating on this
one; everybody flipping quickly.
Reveal.
Everybody says Amber, including
Amber.
( laughter )
So you fully own up to using sex
appeal.
>> I fully own up to it.
>> PROBST: Everybody gets a chop
again.
Alicia, you're up.
>> Amber, since you're going to
use it as a weapon, how about...
>> PROBST: Amber going to take
her first hit.
>> PROBST: Jenna.
>> And payback.
>> PROBST: Amber takes her
second hit.
Shii Ann, you going to put
her out?
>> This is hard.
Rupert doesn't have one, but,
Jenna, I have to take you out
just because.
>> PROBST: And with that, Jenna
was completely beheaded.
Amber's got some payback.
>> Sorry, Alicia.
>> Hey, it's all right.
>> PROBST: Alicia takes her
second hit.
Rupert, why are you laughing?
>> Shii Ann, she's got to stop
telling people to hit me.
>> PROBST: Uh-oh.
( others groaning )
>> Oh...!
>> PROBST: Shii Ann takes it
right between the eyes.
Boston Rob.
>> No need in keeping the
stragglers around.
>> All right, go ahead.
( others groaning )
>> PROBST: Bye-bye, Alicia.
We are down to three.
Who is under the false
assumption that they are smart?
Reveal.
Amber says Tom.
Rupert says himself.
Boston Rob says Jenna.
You're all wrong.
The group thought Alicia was
most under the false assumption
that she was smart.
>> I don't like these people
anymore, let me tell you
something.
>> PROBST: You're taking some
hits today.
>> I'm taking some hits today,
that's all right.
>> PROBST: Next question.
Who did the group think was the
most honest?
Reveal.
Amber and Rupert say Rupert.
Rob said himself.
Correct answer, Rupert.
Amber and Rupert are right.
Amber, you are up.
You only have two choices.
Boston Rob has taken one hit,
Rupert has taken no hits.
>> Sorry, Rob.
>> PROBST: Rob down to his
last pop.
Rupert could put him out of the
game right here.
>> I have to.
>> You could put her out.
>> I could, but Amber didn't
hit me.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Boston Rob is no
more.
Boston Rob, have a seat.
Here's where we're at.
Rupert, you still have three
hits left.
Amber, you only have one.
If Rupert gets this right, he
will obliterate you and win
the challenge.
"Who never shuts up?"
Reveal.
You both say Jenna.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You're both right.
( laughter )
Amber, your hit doesn't really
matter.
Rupert, you get the final
honors.
Take Amber out.
>> Nice job, Rupert.
>> Thank you all, you guys.
>> PROBST: Rupert, with that,
wins reward.
Rupert, you will be in charge of
the menu tonight.
The boat will come and pick
you up.
You guys can now head back
to camp.
♪ ♪
>> You guys gave that one to me.
I appreciate that one.
Thank you, guys.
>> That was awesome.
>> I think the biggest
thing that happened at our
reward challenge today was,
Alicia got all upset again.
She was mocked by the tribe as
the person least deserving to be
an all-star.
Her ego took a blow, but you
know, people say things for a
reason, so maybe she needs to
take a look at herself.
I thought they were pretty good.
The, uh... the masks, too.
>> I thought the masks
were pretty good.
>> You know, it's never
fun to hear things about
yourself that aren't flattering
and then have to... the same
people that said those things,
you're stuck with them.
That's not fun.
>> It would be nice to get out
of camp tonight.
Alicia, you okay?
>> I'm fabulous, baby.
>> Okay. If it helps, I'm
a big mouth.
>> Yeah, but did everybody
say that you don't deserve to
be here and that you definitely
think you're smart and you're
not?
Did people say that about you?
>> Let's say there's only seven.
Let's say....
>> It doesn't matter, dude.
It's already been said. Done.
>> Alicia's very emotional.
And when something upsets her,
she becomes a huge grump around
the camp.
She's just being a big baby
about it.
People are observing it.
People are getting annoyed
with it.
People will vote you out sooner
because they don't want to
live with it.
>> Don't, don't, don't, don't.
>> I know you don't want
somebody to talk to you, but
I'm a mom, it's my job.
>> Yeah, but you know what?
You're not my mom, so it's
all good.
>> But you're hurt.
>> Well, you know what?
That's just the way it goes.
I don't want anybody hugging me
or touching me or trying to...
Leave me alone.
The only person that tried to
not give me my space was Jenna.
Jenna's trying to put her arm
around me.
Give me a break.
Jenna and I have no connection
at all.
I mean, she's probably one of
the people that voted that way
anyway.
So she needs to save it.
Jenna would be the last person
that I would go to for
consoling, the last person.
>> Listen, I know you got a
really big decision, and I
know you're the most generous
person out here, probably.
And just know that we understand
where your position is.
But I'd like to have the choice
is all I'm asking.
>> Okay. That's a great idea.
>> Like if you said, "This is my
decision for the order," and
then just give us choices.
>> That's a great idea.
You know, that's almost a
challenge I wish I didn't win.
This is what killed me on Pearl
Islands was, I let the pecking
order be known and then I was
the next one gone.
>> But don't be a martyr and be
like, "I'm going to take the
smallest one and put everyone
else above me 'cause you need to
be strong, too, okay?
I just don't think you should
give away your big one.
I love Rupert, but strategy-
wise, he is-- I don't want to
say not good at the game, he is,
but he needs some coaching.
>> Seven of us...
>> I do say Shii Ann gets the
rice.
>> Shii Ann gets the rice.
>> But I think we keep ourselves
strong, us four.
We have the numbers.
>> They can't hurt us.
>> No, they can't.
>> This adventure is geared to
create hard feelings between
people.
I hate being that person that
creates the hard feelings.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Welcome to the Romantica
Restaurant.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Rupert, you're at the
head of the table.
>> Cool.
>> PROBST: Everybody else head
in this way and take a seat.
So, Rupert, it's your reward.
Good news is, you get your first
choice of anything here you
want.
We got a big piece of steak,
shrimp, all the fixings.
The bad news is, you have to
allocate the rest and somebody's
going to end up with a very cold
bowl of rice and water from
your own camp.
So, let me go over the rest of
your choices.
We have potatoes with tap water.
Then we have a salad with tap
water that's been chilled.
And we have a ham and cheese
sandwich with some sparkling
water and a little bit of lemon.
We also have a hot dog, sour
kraut and orange juice.
Then we have a big cheeseburger
and french fry plate.
So, you can start with myself.
You can start anywhere you want.
>> I'm going to start with me
and I'm taking the steak.
>> PROBST: All right.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> PROBST: Along with the steak,
open bar, for you only.
You just tell him what you want
to drink and he'll keep
refilling it.
>> We'll start with a cerveza.
>> PROBST: All right.
Rupert's starting with a beer.
So, this is on you.
It's your menu.
You're going to distribute it.
>> I would like Rob to choose
next.
>> PROBST: One ice-cold cola and
the burger.
>> I'd like Jenna to choose
next.
>> PROBST: Going right down the
line.
Orange juice.
>> I would like Amber to choose
next.
>> PROBST: Ham and cheese
sandwich, sparkling water.
All right, Rupert, three items
left.
>> Alicia?
>> I would love the salad.
>> PROBST: Salad and cold water.
>> Thank you.
I probably would have chose
that.
>> Very good.
>> PROBST: That worked out.
>> Big Tom, what do you want?
>> PROBST: Big Tom picks next.
>> Whatever...
What is that?
>> Potatoes.
>> I'll eat some potatoes.
Potatoes, yeah.
>> Leave the Asian girl with
the rice.
>> Yeah.
( chuckling )
>> We went to one of the
fanciest restaurants.
They said it was five-star.
>> Please don't stab me.
( chuckling )
>> But I wouldn't hit a dog
in the hind end with it 'cause
I got a tater and it was cold.
>> Shii Ann... camp.
>> PROBST: Camp water and cold
rice.
>> I hope it's boiled, both the
rice and the camp water.
>> PROBST: A little bit of an
awkward dinner, but it's a
dinner nonetheless.
You're warm for a little while.
I'll get out of your hair.
Bon appétit.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
>> This camp water tastes better
out here because of the romantic
lighting.
>> Good.
>> You saw the people that
ended up with fifth, sixth and
seventh weren't too happy about
the politics that were involved,
but hey, what can you do
about that?
You win some, you lose some.
>> Those fries look so good.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> I'm chewing my rice
and thinking that I'm eating
that piece of steak that
Rupert's holding in his hands.
>> I can't even look up at
you guys.
>> Don't look up.
Just eat.
Shii Ann's an absolutely
obnoxious person.
The whole time she's like, "This
rice is good.
Oh, my gosh, ooh, look at that
steak, I just want to watch you
eat it."
>> I wish I could give you guys
all some.
>> I know.
>> Shut up!
It's obnoxious!
>> Thank you, sir.
( chuckling )
Big Tom, I'm drinking this
for you.
( Rupert burping )
>> So the dinner was nice.
And Rupert, of course, had eight
or nine beers and he was
plastered.
Plastered!
>> Thank you, sir.
( burping )
>> Smell your napkin.
>> It's so nice and soft.
( Rupert laughing )
>> I'm taking...
We're taking advantage of this.
>> Good.
>> Rupert, keep drinking.
>> Okay.
>> We really wanted to stay at
the restaurant for as long as
we possibly could, 'cause we
just dreaded coming back here
with all the bugs and the really
long night.
So, we told Rupert, "Keep
drinking as much as you want."
We're just going to lay here on
the table and use these napkins
as pillows and enjoy it.
>> Rupert's a happy man.
( Rupert chuckling )
>> Basically, Rupert
exposed our alliance of four.
It was pretty evident, uh...
as to who got what food.
He's kind of sticking it in
their face, which kind of shows
me that he does trust myself and
Amber to a degree.
>> ♪ Chaboga Mogo, Chaboga
Mogo, Chaboga Mogo... ♪
The sun is out, and we're going
to have a beautiful day.
>> We are going to have a
beautiful day.
>> I'm going to battle 'cause
I got to, but I'm not going
to kill myself to win 'cause
I hope that I'm not on the
chopping block.
>> I don't think you are.
>> And I wouldn't mind seeing
you win immunity.
>> You got to be looking at Rob.
I would be if I were you.
>> Oh, my gosh...
>> If I were anyone here, I'd
would be looking at Rob.
>> I've already talked to Jenna
about that.
>> Of course, you have.
>> But they're telling me
they'll take me to the final
four, too, but I know I'll be
fourth unless I win immunity.
>> There are people here
that would stretch their vote
tonight if they felt like they
had the majority.
>> Yeah.
>> We know that.
>> I know that.
>> There are people here.
>> Let me... hand me...
while you're over, give me
that solid piece!
See that good little piece
right here?
>> Yep.
So, uh... who's up on the...?
>> Chop block?
>> Yep.
>> ( whispering ): It's him
before Shii Ann.
>> Rupert before Shii Ann.
I was thinking about that today.
I was looking at everybody
today, and I was kind of...
sizing up.
>> All I'm saying, we got...
me and you got to stick
together, Alicia.
>> Absolutely.
And I'll tell you what, though,
if either one of us are up
against Amber or Boston Rob,
we're in trouble.
>> But you know as well as I do,
me and you are the lone horse
here.
>> Yep.
And those two are going to stick
together no matter what.
>> They're lovers.
>> I know.
>> But you know what?
We may have not slept together,
but we... we snuggled pretty
close.
>> That's right.
We decided, Big Tom, Rob, Amber
and myself, that we were going
to stay together to the very
end.
That's four people.
So, no matter what happens in
this tribe, we are four to the
to the other three.
Then there's Big Tom.
He came to me and said, you
know, "I can't sit next to
Boston Rob or Amber.
I'll never win.
Maybe I should sit next to you."
And I said, "You know what?
Maybe you're right."
But I didn't make any deal
with him.
The only person I have an
alliance with at this point is
Boston Rob, and we shook on it.
But do I trust him?
Absolutely not.
>> Here's the thing.
If Shii Ann wins immunity
today...
>> It'd be a miracle.
>> Yeah, I know, but still, we
have to decide.
>> Rob, let's just face it,
it's gonna hurt you more than
it will me.
You got a better chance at
winning than I have.
>> I need to win, like,
almost every one, Tom.
I know what people think around
the camp.
I know even though Rupert
pretends he's all nice-- last
night he gave me a hamburger--
I can read beyond that,
you know?
If Shii Ann wins immunity, I
don't know who we're gonna
kick off.
>> You're worried about
Shii Ann.
I'm worried about Rupert.
Because he's the one that's
gonna beat you in an immunity.
Shii Ann ain't gonna beat you.
>> All right.
>> Uh, Alicia ain't gonna
beat you.
But we can't beat Rupert.
You're gonna come close, but
he's gonna beat you before
it's over.
>> Right.
>> And then when he does, you
know who they want to get
rid of?
It ain't gonna be me.
>> No, it'll be me.
>> It's you.
>> Yeah, we should talk,
actually.
I have some news.
>> I don't want to even hear it.
Honestly.
>> That's fine.
>> There is a plan, Shii Ann,
and it's too late for anything
to change.
>> Okay. I appreciate that.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: There's no denying
it-- we are getting down to it.
There are seven of you left.
Today's challenge is for
immunity.
Very important at this stage
of the game.
It's a very simple immunity
challenge.
You're gonna step up on a log.
You're gonna raise your hand
over your head.
Your hand is gonna be tethered
to a bucket.
That bucket's full of water.
When you drop your hand, the
bucket tips, you get wet,
you're done.
If you need immunity, the only
thing stopping you from getting
it is quitting, and that's it.
We got all day to sit out here.
All right, Boston Rob, give
it up.
The all-important immunity is
back up for grabs.
Take your spots.
I'll lock you in.
For immunity.
Everybody's locked in, and this
challenge is officially on.
There'll be a little initial
pain.
You'll work through that.
Just remember, there's not a lot
of slack in that chain, so if
you drop your hand two inches,
you're done.
You have very little wiggle room
in this challenge.
Amber's first out.
Grab a seat on the bench.
>> I didn't even move!
>> PROBST: Jenna's out of the
game.
>> You didn't need that immunity
anyway.
It's all good.
>> Nobody knows who's safe.
>> I know I'm not safe, that's
for sure.
>> PROBST: Have a seat next to
Amber.
Big Tom, you're struggling.
>> Oh, Big Tom.
>> PROBST: Big Tom, third person
to hit the dust.
>> Okay, Rupert, you
got to hold out before Rob.
>> PROBST: Big Tom's out of the
challenge.
>> We can't let Rob keep winning
these immunities.
>> Damn straight.
>> PROBST: Have a seat next to
the ladies, Big Tom.
You're out of the challenge.
>> I see Shii Ann's arm moving a
bit, so you guys are good.
>> PROBST: So, Jenna, I take it
from that comment there's just
no secrets in this tribe
right now.
>> No. No, there isn't.
>> Oh, there are secrets to
this tribe.
No secret on who they want out
tonight, but there's secrets
to this tribe.
>> PROBST: Alicia fighting
through a little pain.
>> Be strong, Alicia.
>> PROBST: First sign of
weakness we've seen from Alicia
on this.
Fight, guys.
It's all about this right here.
That sound around your neck.
It means you're in this game a
little longer.
It means you've got a one-in-six
shot at a million bucks.
Somebody gonna leave here with
this.
The person who wants it the
most.
Fight it, guys, fight it. Oh!
Whew!
I got a little of that, too.
>> All right! I'm glad.
At least if I went down, I took
you with me.
>> PROBST: I couldn't be
happier.
>> Keep your arm up, Rupert.
Keep your arm up.
>> I'm damn straight trying.
>> PROBST: And then there were
three.
All three looking really strong.
A little bit of rain starting to
come down, cool you off a
little.
Wouldn't be a day on Survivor:
All-Star if we didn't get a
little rain.
( thunder crashing )
Immunity is most definitely up
for grabs.
Three people left.
Anybody could get it.
Shii Ann, I have to say, one
hour in, you have not moved.
Your body has not moved, your
arm has not dipped.
>> I'm not moving.
>> PROBST: I don't think you've
taken your hand off your hip.
>> Nope.
It's numb, but I need this
immunity, like I said, Jeff,
desperately.
( Jenna mouthing words )
( birds twittering )
( insect buzzing )
>> PROBST: Boston Rob's out of
the competition.
Next-door neighbors Rupert and
Shii Ann still fighting for
immunity.
Since it's just down to you two,
a little reminder:
Somebody's gonna leave here with
this around their neck.
That means they are safe tonight
at the vote.
The other person will not have
that same security.
>> Rupert, stay up there.
>> You got this, Rupert.
( thunder rolling )
( birds chirping )
>> PROBST: You guys have lasted
two hours.
Two long, painful hours.
How much more you got left in
you, Rupert?
Shii Ann, any sign of quitting
in you?
>> Nope.
( rain pouring )
>> Careful, Rupert,
you're moving it a lot.
You're moving the chain.
>> Yes! Yes! Yes!
>> PROBST: Rupert's out of the
competition.
Shii Ann wins immunity.
>> Whoo! Whoo!!
Yeah! Take that!
( grunts )
>> Don't forget, you got
to go home with us, Shii Ann.
Be very careful, sweetheart.
>> Hey, you know what?
I love you guys, but I need this
more than all of you guys.
>> Yeah, don't get too cocky,
though.
You got to live with us.
>> I needed it more than all
of you guys.
>> PROBST: All right, Shii Ann,
turn around.
Looks like you're about ready
to cry.
You doing all right?
>> I'm doing great.
They're tears of joy.
I knew I was going home tonight,
and now...
>> PROBST: It most definitely
will not be you.
Great effort.
You are safe tonight at Tribal
Council.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Guaranteed a
one-in-six shot of winning this
thing and the million bucks.
For the rest of you, I can't
say the same thing.
Somebody is going home tonight.
Tribal Council.
I'll see you there.
Go back to camp.
♪ ♪
( chirping )
( fire crackling )
>> I didn't mean to get so
excited.
I wasn't trying to gloat.
I was just...
Really wanted to win.
>> Everybody gets excited when
they win immunity or reward.
>> Just today, I really needed
it, so I got a little excited.
>> That's all right.
>> The thing that bothered me
about Shii Ann's victory is that
she tried to throw it in our
face the moment she won.
And the first thing she does is
let out this victory cry, and
she's, like, "Yeah! Ha! I did
it!" You know?
She's pointing at all of us, and
I just looked at her and said,
"I wouldn't be that cocky-- you
still have to live with us."
>> I'm feeling a whole
lot better now that these proud
little Chaboga Mogos are gonna
have to eat one of their own.
I love the fact that they're all
sitting there squirming in
their... shorts, ignoring me
yet again.
They should have been cutting
deals with me before my
immunity win.
Now that I have an immunity win,
I know that Alicia's head is on
the chopping block, Rob
Mariano's head's on the chopping
block, and so is Rupert's.
Stupid people.
Let me just say that again:
stupid players.
You know, your head is big-time
on the chopping block today.
>> Oh, I know.
I'm taking all my stuff to
Tribal Council with me.
>> I'm telling you,
Rob is the person to get rid of
because he's the kingpin.
You got to work it or else
you're going.
>> Oh, I know.
( bird squawking )
>> Shii Ann's a deal maker.
Such a strategist.
Look at her down there.
Look at the strategizing going
on right now.
I have two options tonight.
I can stick with Rupert and
Jenna, myself and Amber to make
that foursome, or I can go with
Big Tom, Alicia, Amber and
myself...
and take out Rupert or Jenna,
'cause I don't know if Rupert
and Jenna are like 100% with us.
I like to say Alicia is out
of here.
She is. She's out of here.
Maybe not. Maybe me.
>> For me, it's between
probably Rupert or Alicia.
>> You prefer Alicia.
>> I don't know.
>> For me, it would be between
Rupert and Rob, because
I think one of them needs to go.
They're too big and too
powerful.
You feel more comfortable with
Rob; you trust him more 'cause
you're...
>> Well, I... I trust him
more and I think that even if
I'm lying to him, he's gonna
trust me.
>> She's so sweet.
You hate to hate her because
she's so lovely and she's got
those beautiful green eyes, but
you know what?
She is one of the shrewdest
players out here.
>> "We love you.
We can't wait for you to come
home and be a family.
Wherever you are, I know you're
kicking some ass.
Remember, the key to the game is
loose lips sink ships."
>> What?
>> Honestly, if I didn't
trust you 100%, I would never
let you read this, but, you
know...
>> "Remember, the key to
the game is loose lips..."
>> My main alliance still
is with Amber.
It's because she trusts me
completely; even though I may
not trust her 100% completely, I
know she does.
I think she does.
( bird squawks )
We can do this.
We're going to do this.
You know that?
We gotta just keep the paranoia
to a minimum before Tribal
Councils.
We gotta trust in a game like
this.
It's like huge, you know?
It makes all the difference in
the world, and I appreciate it.
Of course she's playing the
game.
She may be playing me, I don't
know.
I don't think so.
I really don't.
I think it's genuine what's
going on.
I could be the biggest sucker in
history, and if so, hey--
she had me fooled.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Now bring in the
members of our jury, Lex and
Kathy, voted out the last Tribal
Council.
I'll remind you guys that the
jury's here merely to observe.
They're not to talk to you.
You're not to try and
communicate with them.
It's been a busy couple of days,
culminating with a very big and,
from what I gather today,
important victory at today's
immunity challenge for you,
Shii Ann.
>> Yes, very, very
important.
>> You were very vocal today
and, from where I sat, sort of
created an island for yourself.
>> This tribe is very
unique in that they've been
very, very open with me about
the fact that they are a tight
alliance and I'm going home
next.
So, you know, today at the
challenge, I was very vocal,
because I'm going to try my best
to fight.
>> PROBST: Rupert, what's your
take on everything that went
down today?
>> That was one heck of
a hard challenge.
After 20 minutes, I was dying.
Shii Ann says she was the only
one that needed it, but now
somebody else needs it.
There's been talk that I'm
targeted.
I felt like, especially with
that silly reward challenge over
the pecking-order caca, I'm up.
I mean, my number could be up.
>> PROBST: Alicia, we have four
from the original Chapera.
You guys have the numbers.
How strong is that group still?
>> Well, the original Chapera
is-is always going to be
strong because we've been
together from the day one, but
we also could not have done it
without Rupert and Jenna joining
our tribe.
Honestly, we knew that once we
got to six, game on.
Anything can happen and any one
of us is vulnerable at this
point.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann, did you
notice a power shift today?
Were you the person in camp
people wanted to come talk to
and try and make a deal?
>> No. I-I...
You know, it's so funny.
What I notice about this group
of six is that, as far as I can
tell, no one wants to take a
leadership position and say this
person in particular is getting
voted out tonight.
>> PROBST: Jenna, you were
rolling your head all over the
place.
>> 'Cause it makes us sound
dumb.
>> No, no, no, I don't
think...
>> PROBST: Hold off. Shii Ann.
>> I mean, maybe we're not
telling Shii Ann everything
because we don't need her to
know our strategies.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob, first
time in a while, you haven't had
that necklace around your neck.
You're a provider, very strong,
seem to be a likable guy.
Why not get rid of you while we
have the opportunity?
>> What are you giving
them ideas for, Jeff?
>> PROBST: It had to have
crossed your mind.
>> Of course.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sitting here, I won the
first two immunities, I've been
strong pretty much, I think, the
whole game.
I'm definitely nervous tonight,
and I wish I had that necklace
on.
>> PROBST: On that note, it's
time to vote.
Shii Ann, you have immunity.
I know you don't want to give it
away, but I'll go ahead and ask.
>> No, Jeff, I'm not
going to give it away.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Shii Ann.
Everybody else is fair game.
Let's vote. Amber, you're up.
♪ ♪
>> Remember the little
fight we had on day three,
where I zipped my lip?
I've been waiting to do this for
27 days, so...
au revoir, adios, arrivederci,
sayonara, or as we say in
Boston, see you later.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Alicia.
Alicia. Two votes Alicia.
Rupert.
Two votes Alicia, one vote
Alicia.
Twelfth person voted out of
Survivor: All-Stars,
and the third member of our
jury, Alicia.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Well, somebody turned.
I'd better not find out who
it is.
>> PROBST: Alicia, the tribe has
spoken.
>> PROBST: Well, Shii Ann was
very open tonight in sharing
that she was treated with
respect and honesty regarding
her status in the tribe.
Clearly, that doesn't apply to
members of your own family of
six, as Alicia never saw it
coming.
Nine days left, guys.
Grab your torches.
Go back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
>> ANNOUNCER: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Jenna and Shii Ann want each
other gone...
>> Yeah, I'm not having
plantains today.
You want them, you cook them
for yourself.
>> I want to strangle her.
>> She opens her mouth, and I
feel like putting a gun in mine.
>> PROBST: ...while Rupert and
Jenna have been together
too long.
>> I was cooking.
>> She's just a pain in the ass
and I'm very sorry that I have
an alliance with her.
>> Here I sit, voted out, third
member of the jury.
I wish you all luck.
As for Boston Rob, you had a
handshake with me, so I'm really
hoping that you're not sitting
in the final two, because now
I sit on the jury and believe
me, when I have to decide who
actually gets the million
dollars, I'm not going to
make it easy.