>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor...
For the first time, 18 former
castaways return to the game as
three tribes, Chapera, Mogo Mogo
and Saboga.
And they soon found out just how
crucial fire would be.
( grunting )
>> This ain't a little
boy's game.
This is for the big boys.
>> PROBST: Because no fire meant
no water.
>> You can't drink it
right out of the well.
There's potential brain
parasites.
>> PROBST: At Saboga, Rudy
approached Rupert with a plan.
>> Me and you ought to
think about an alliance.
>> He and I will stick
together through the end of the
game.
>> PROBST: And at Chapera,
Boston Rob and Amber made a
connection.
>> What do you think?
You want to make an alliance?
>> I don't know if I can
take you seriously or not.
>> I'm being 100 percent
serious.
>> PROBST: Go!
In a very close immunity
challenge, Saboga fell behind,
giving Chapera and Mogo Mogo
shared immunity.
( cheering )
Back at camp, Jenna campaigned
to vote out the previous
winners.
>> Tonight, I think
it's important to take out the
two winners first.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Ethan felt vulnerable.
But Tina was the first All-Star
voted out.
Tina, the tribe has spoken.
With all the tribes denied fire
for three days, the castaways
face severe dehydration.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( theme song playing )
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> Coming back from Tribal
Council without fire was
devastating.
With Tina gone, pouring rain,
dying of thirst, them thinking
that we're going to bring fire
home.
So, we leave a pot of water--
of well water, contaminated
water-- in the pot instead of an
open, empty pot to catch rain
water is a bad way to end day
three.
>> I don't think I've ever gone
this long without food.
>> Last night was the
most miserable night of my life.
I tried to sleep.
I didn't get a single wink of
sleep all night long.
I sat upright in the shelter all
night, rocking back and forth,
trying to stay warm, 'cause we
were all soaking wet.
>> Vietnam was the same as
this place, you know.
You get wet, and...
>> You stay wet?
>> ...and your boots
never dried.
>> You were in Vietnam?
>> Yeah, we were down in
the Mekong Delta.
>> You ever scared?
>> Was I scared?
Yeah, for a whole year.
( chuckling )
>> Rudy is one of a kind.
He sleeps on the ground when the
rest of us are squeezing
together in our shelter.
And he was drinking well water
before we could boil safely,
even after we'd been told
specifically that there are some
crazy parasites in there that
will put you in a coma.
Rudy, are you still drinking
that well water?
>> Oh, yes, he is.
>> Well, at this
point, he's drank so much.
( laughing )
>> It doesn't taste like
rot?
>> I'm still standing at
noon, don't drink it.
( chuckling )
>> Water contamination
will hit you pretty quick.
But once Rudy decides he wants
to drink the well water, there's
no telling him no.
He does what he wants.
>> There used to be a
little bar next to where we
lived in Utah.
You know, they'd serve ice,
which was rare.
And I asked them, "Where did you
get the water?"
They said the reservoir.
At any given time, you could see
six bodies floating around in
that reservoir, you know?
>> Aw...
>> Did you drink it with
ice?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, geez.
>> And I should worry
about this?
>> Wow.
( chuckles )
>> Dehydration may be our
biggest concern at this point.
We haven't been able to achieve
fire, thus we have not been able
to boil the water from our water
source.
>> Our tongues had
turned white.
It was just so hot.
We were just dying of thirst.
>> Initially, the rain
came, and you're thinking,
"Okay, I got to keep dry."
But after a few minutes of that,
the light bulb went on.
And all of us realized that
fresh water was falling from the
sky.
>> I never thought I'd
be so happy to see tropical
rain.
We were like animals gone wild.
I mean, we had to have water.
That water was so sweet.
>> I think if it keeps
going like this for a few more
minutes, I'll drink my fill.
>> Hopefully, it'll
rain for quite a while.
It's nice and warm.
It's just wet, wet, wet, wet,
wet.
>> My take on Richard's
choice to be, you know, a nudist
out here... honestly it doesn't
bother me in the least.
Every time he drops trou, and
comes just stumbling back into
camp without a stitch of
clothing on, it was hilarious.
>> It's nice out there.
It's not cold.
My thing is, sitting under there
trying to avoid drops, it gets
cold.
>> The bad part is, the
rest of us are becoming
comfortable with it.
That's what's even spooky.
We got an overweight, gay, naked
man walking around, and no one
seems to let it bother them.
I don't know.
Unfortunately, I think he wants
us all to be naked and natural
walking around.
That I don't see happening.
>> ♪ We got some water
We got some water. ♪
>> Whoo!
>> You would have thought
that maybe we were drinking
champagne, but it was just
getting water from the rain.
>> ♪ Nobody knows
The words
♪ But it's all good today
And I know
We're going to drink ♪
>> ♪ Some water
♪ I want to know
Have you ever seen the rain?
♪ Coming down
Over me... ♪
( laughing )
( cheering )
( chanting )
>> Uh-oh.
>> "Don't open.
Very valuable. Keep dry."
>> We see a big crate,
and there's three padlocks on
the crate.
So, we have no idea what's
inside.
>> It looks like we're
playing for a set of keys, yeah?
>> I don't know.
It feels like something
substantial, whatever it is.
>> Maybe it's an animal.
It's always interesting when
they give you boxes.
You know, you go through all the
options of what you'd want to be
in there...
>> Food.
>> Matches or something.
>> Anything, at this point,
that you get to open is fun,
'cause it's like a gift.
>> They brought this
so we could stare at it and
wonder what's in it for the next
two hours.
>> This is, like,
such a tease.
>> Hold on, hold on...
>> Oh, yeah, I tried...
>> Hold on.
I just had an idea.
You guys want to open it?
When we first got that box, my
first inclination was,
"Forget about the note.
We're starving over here."
We just smash it open.
>> No, I don't want to ruin
our chances at anything...
>> You win the
challenge, the challenge...
>> But then, all of a
sudden, everybody else was
saying, "Oh, no, we don't want
to do that.
We might upset Pretty Boy Probst
or something."
( chanting )
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Mogo Mogo, Chapera getting their
first look at the new Saboga
tribe.
Tina voted out, first Tribal
Council.
Okay, let's get to today's
reward challenge.
We're building a staircase to
the stars.
Here's how it works.
There are five logs tethered out
in the ocean.
On my "go," five members of each
tribe will swim out and get the
furthest log.
Once there, you'll unclip the
log, bring it back, put it in
the staircase as the first leg.
Then four tribe members, then
three, then two, until we get to
the last log.
One tribe member will retrieve
the final log, place it in the
staircase.
First tribe to get all five
pieces and get to the top of the
platform wins reward.
This is going to be grueling,
especially for your anchors,
'cause they're swimming every
leg.
Now, you want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Please.
>> PROBST: Blankets.
Keep you warm at night.
>> That's nice.
>> PROBST: Come in handy.
Chapera, Mogo Mogo, 'cause you
have one extra member, you're
sitting somebody out.
Keeping in mind, you cannot sit
out the same person in
back-to-back challenges.
Chapera, who's sitting out?
>> Big Tom.
>> PROBST: Big Tom. Mogo Mogo,
who's sitting out?
>> Jenna.
>> PROBST: Jenna.
Everybody else, wait for my
"go."
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, guys.
>> Whoo-ya! Let's go!
Come on, Big Red!
>> PROBST: Swimming out to the
furthest log first.
>> Let's suck some seawater!
Let's go!
>> PROBST: Chapera first at
their log.
Unclips, heading back.
Saboga heading back.
Moga Mogo heading back.
We're dead even.
Stay with that log, guys.
Stay with your log.
>> Stay with the log.
You got it. Let's go!
Go right. What are you doing?
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Got to be together.
>> Come on, Rudy.
We need you, buddy.
Come on, Rudy.
Come on.
>> PROBST: Jenna working with
Rudy.
>> Come on!
You just have to get to the
beach.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo together.
Chapera's together.
>> Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Hang in there, Rudy.
You're there.
Place it once you have it in.
>> I got to get some air.
>> PROBST: All three tribes are
neck and neck.
Shii Ann is sitting out for Mogo
Mogo.
Rudy taking a sit.
Alicia taking a sit.
Four tribe members now swimming
out for the fourth log.
Let's go, keep moving!
You can rest tonight.
Saboga has their second log.
Mogo Mogo has their second log.
>> Let's go, guys!
>> PROBST: Chapera unhooked and
heading back!
>> Let's go, guys!
Let's go!
>> PROBST: Saboga first out the
water.
Mogo Mogo right behind them.
Saboga with their second step in
the ladder.
>> ( groans loudly )
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo heading
back out.
Here comes Chapera.
>> Let's go, guys!
>> PROBST: Jenna sitting out.
Kathy sitting out.
Rob, Amber, Sue, going back.
Swimming really taking its toll.
>> They're slowing down.
Hell!
The turtle wins the race!
>> PROBST: Saboga has their
third log, heading back.
Mogo Mogo has their third log,
heading back.
Sue, Rob and Amber still
struggling.
>> Come on, guys!
>> Come on, guys, please!
>> PROBST: Once again, Saboga
first out of the water.
>> PROBST: Can't put it in till
everybody's there.
>> You're so close!
>> PROBST: Let's go, Mogo Mogo.
You're still in this.
>> Come on, you can do it.
>> PROBST: Rupert and Ethan
heading back out.
>> Come on, you guys!
>> PROBST: Lex and Richard
heading back out for Mogo Mogo
while Chapera comes in with
their third log.
Boston Rob and Sue heading back
out.
Can they close the gap?
Saboga with the big lead.
>> Come on, you guys!
>> PROBST: Rupert looking strong
as ever.
Ethan right there with him.
>> Come on! Hurry up!
>> Come on, let's go!
>> Guys, come on!
>> PROBST: Saboga again first
out of the water.
Mogo Mogo on their tail.
>> Let's go!
>> Catch up!
Let's go, Mogo Mogo.
You're still in this.
Ethan taking the last leg for
Saboga.
>> Go! Go! Go!
>> PROBST: Hatch has a lot of
ground to make up on Ethan.
Can he do it?
Mariano taking the last leg for
Chapera.
>> You're catching up!
Let's go!
>> This is everything, Ethan.
Come on.
>> Come on, Ethan!
>> Ethan, we love you!
>> PROBST: A lot of swimming
with no food and no water in
your belly.
Boston Rob having a tough time.
>> Go... Ethan.
>> PROBST: Ethan close to
winning it for Saboga.
Hatch still a lot of ground to
make up.
Ethan with the final log for
Saboga.
Got to get to the top.
>> Go, Ethan, go!
>> PROBST: Saboga wins reward.
>> You did it.
And we showed them.
>> Get in here, Rudy.
>> PROBST: All right.
Saboga, congratulations.
And your reward, blankets.
>> Yay.
>> PROBST: Before you take the
blankets, I want to make a
proposition to you.
Each tribe today received a
lock box.
I'm going to tell you what's in
the lock box: Rice.
>> ALL: Oh!
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: Only problem is, that
lock box and the rice in it does
you no good, because you need
three keys to get it open, and
even if you had it open without
fire, you can't cook the rice.
So, here's the offer.
You can trade the blankets for
this-- the first clue to finding
the first key to get in your
lock box.
Flint.
You'll have a constant source of
fire, and a pot to cook that
rice in.
There's a rub.
If you take...
the pot with the clue and the
map and the flint instead of the
blankets, Mogo Mogo gets it, as
well as Chapera.
>> Oh.
( all talking )
>> Is that good with
you?
>> What are you going to do?
>> I say we still take
it, give everybody.
>> Give everybody...
>> Oh!
>> Yes!
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Thank you.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Here you go.
I'm throwing it up.
( cheering )
>> Toss it up here, Jeffy.
>> I can't believe they
ousted Tina.
>> Holy...
>> Oh, my God, that is...
That is such a shock.
>> I would have put a
lot of money that Rudy was gone.
Holy crap.
That thing kind of blew me out
of the water.
Tina, first one out.
Big targets on the winners,
except me.
No.
It was a big target on me.
Ha!
We'll see.
>> Me, I'm surprised, but
at the same time, it's cool,
because it sets the tone for the
whole game.
>> There's no...
>> Tina's first out.
We all know what...
It's business this time.
>> It was tough.
That was probably the toughest
challenge I've ever
experienced...
>> That might be the hardest
challenge I've done
on Survivor.
>> ...in any Survivor.
>> When we showed up to
the challenge, and I saw Tina
was voted out of the game, that
made me very excited, because I
think that she's a big phony.
And if it means that the winners
are going next, that's all right
by me.
But the last time I checked, I
didn't have a million dollars
yet.
>> You want to get some
fire going?
>> Let's try to get the
fire.
Let's go, Tommy, first try.
There it is, there it is, there
it is.
>> Yeah, there's a
coating on the flint, and you
got to get all the coating off,
and then you can strike it.
>> Big Tom knows what
he's doing.
>> I came back here, and
I knew exactly how to build a
fire and get it started, but of
course, Boston Rob and Big Tom--
these guys are so macho.
They're the men.
They're the men of the tribe.
>> Tommy, you're getting
sparks already.
>> Can we build a nest
right on it and-and light it
from here, as opposed to that
little...?
>> Yeah, let's try to do
it.
>> Because...
>> Well, uh, really that's
great, but, uh...
>> Can I try it?
>> Yeah, try it.
>> Right now, old farm
boy's just got to keep his mouth
shut.
It's too early in the game to be
bossy.
I think we got four or five
bosses and maybe one Indian.
>> Make sure it's fluffy.
>> Want me to scrape a little
bit of the magnesium on there?
>> Yeah, you want air.
>> Yeah, go ahead,
scrape a little magnesium on it.
>> Lots of air.
>> Awesome. That's good.
That's all you have to do.
>> Alicia's just talking
a little bit too much.
>> Don't-don't move away
from the fire.
>> She walks around
giving orders constantly.
It's her nature.
She got a big mouth.
She needs to learn to shut it.
>> You got it.
There you go, you got it.
That's it.
That's all we needed.
Beautiful.
>> Yee-ha!
>> That was...
>> We got it.
We got it going on.
>> There you go.
>> Sweet.
>> There'll be no more
rubbing of sticks together.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh!
( grunts )
>> That was flame.
Oh, my God.
In the first two min...
Oh, my God, I'm getting excited.
>> Our lives are about to
change for the better.
>> It's still going to
be very hard.
This is showing me that I'm
not...
You know, I thought I was an
outdoors man, and I am, with a
lighter.
( laughs )
>> Hello, water.
I don't know.
You're much stronger than I am.
>> You don't think I'm
the biggest...?
After my display today, you
don't think I'm the biggest
target that's out there right
now?
>> Yeah.
I felt really bad for Ethan,
because he knows he's on the
chopping block.
And then, it was even worse at
the reward challenge when he did
so well.
And I went to congratulate him
like I did everyone else, and I
was, like, "Great job."
And he's, like, "Yeah."
'Cause he knows it's all for
naught.
We don't know when we're going
to lose immunity.
We might not lose.
It might be nine days.
Who knows?
Just give it a couple of days
rest, okay?
>> I already had a talk
with Jenna Lewis.
She says, "Well, you know, maybe
we'll keep you around a little
longer, you know, if that's what
you wanted."
Oh, thanks, Jenna.
You know, thanks for granting me
that one wish.
It's like she's, like, so cocky,
calling the shots and stuff, and
it just bugs me.
>> Whoa!
>> Oh, yeah, oh, yeah,
oh, yeah...
>> Wait.
Don't blow too hard, you're just
gonna blow it out.
>> There's a fire.
There's a fire going.
>> Sticks, more sticks.
>> There you are.
There you go.
>> Some more, some more.
More sticks.
>> I'll blow it from
this side.
>> We got plenty of sticks.
Whoo!
>> Jesus! Aah, aah.
Damn it.
I'm all right.
>> Oh, God.
>> Stupid me puts my face
two inches from the fire.
Whap!
It singed all of the hair off
the front of my head, but we
have fire.
It's like the power of the gods.
>> I see that.
>> Yay!
>> We got fire!
Yay!
>> It's joy.
>> It's wet.
Here comes the rain.
>> It starts pouring, we
may need to postpone this.
We made a huge effort to try to
make fire.
I don't know what the deal is.
I don't know if it's... if, at
this point, it's a function of
our materials or our level of
energy that there are too many
conditions that are working
against us, because the
humidity's so high.
>> Oh!
>> Let me blow from the bottom.
>> It's going to pour any
second.
>> No, it's not.
>> Look at that.
>> Should we maybe consider
not making fire until the storm
passes?
>> Until tomorrow morning.
>> Yeah.
>> No.
Why not keep trying?
>> I don't want to waste
material...
>> I mean, we have an
opportunity to make fire.
Why not?
( thunder rumbling )
( rain pouring )
>> Why is it so cold?
>> I hate the fact we don't have
fire.
>> Oh. We should have done the
fire right when we got back.
>> I know.
>> We're freezing because
our lame boys didn't make the
fire.
Lex now regrets how he didn't
get on it, so I'm just trying to
warm up, 'cause we're all
soaking wet.
I'm having a great time.
( birds squawking )
>> We need more fuel,
sticks.
We finally got fire, and, uh, I
mean, fire is everything.
It's food, it's water.
You know, it gives you a
purpose.
Oh, my God, we've got fire.
>> "...past the forest where
roots sprout from the ground,
the outermost point is where it
can be found.
Carved in the side of the hill
is a cave.
Tucked deep inside is the key
that you crave."
>> I think it's that way.
>> We decided to go
look for the key for one of the
three locks on the treasure
chest of what I guess now we
found out is rice.
( squawking )
>> No?
>> No, not that I can find.
>> What?
>> We found it.
>> You did?
>> Put it back.
I wanted to see where it is.
>> Cool box.
>> Here we go.
>> Let's see, let's see, let's
see.
>> Found it, no problem.
It was deep within the cave.
Anybody looking would think of
today as huge, given that we got
water and fire and a key to the
trunk.
That's all extraneous crap to
me.
That's not Survivor.
The game's all the interpersonal
stuff.
Yeah, you roar.
We got it, whoa!
( blows raspberry )
You know, that's outside the
game.
That just isn't in me.
>> Is he still limping?
>> He's kind of stumbling,
even just walking
over those rocks.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> But he's walking.
He's getting around.
He's... you know...
a tough old man.
>> My foot hurts when I
walk.
You know, it, uh... it sort of
makes me limp a little.
I don't know what's wrong.
It... probably in a week, it'll
be back to normal.
>> How's it doing today?
Any better?
No?
>> Not much.
>> Why don't you sit
down, take it easy?
>> I wanted to see if I
could run.
I can't.
>> Rudy's not doing okay.
His feet... he's got a big
blister, but also he did
something to the bone inside
that's been really hurting.
And he tells me he can't walk,
he can't run.
>> I sure hope it's not
a running challenge today,
'cause we'll be dead alive.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Thank you, Amber.
Shii Ann.
Shared immunity for two tribes
back up for grabs.
Ready for today's challenge?
Each tribe will start out an a
floating platform.
On my "go," all five tribe
members will dive out, get to
the bottom of the ocean floor,
where you will find a sunken
boat loaded with 14 very heavy
crates.
Untying a series of slipknots,
you'll release the crates.
Then you have to get the crates
out of your boat.
Once all 14 crates are out, the
boat will float to the top.
You'll drag it back to your
platform, flip it over and start
bailing out the water.
You get your paddles.
It is a race back to shore.
The first two tribes to cross
the finish line with all members
and their boat wins immunity.
Chapera, Mogo Mogo, because you
have extra members, you're
sitting somebody out.
For Chapera, who's sitting out
this one?
Alicia. Mogo Mogo?
All right, Shii Ann.
Everybody else, swim out.
Here we go, guys.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Everybody got to get a hand on
the pontoon.
Start diving!
>> We got them all.
>> Okay.
>> I got two boxes off.
>> PROBST: Take your time.
2,000 pounds of weight in that
boat.
( indistinct voices )
>> Oh!
( splutters )
>> I got one.
( coughs )
>> PROBST: Jenna heads back for
Saboga to the platform.
>> Go, Rupert.
It's right there.
>> PROBST: Saboga, the first
tribe with their boat up,
dragging their boat back to the
platform.
Saboga at the platform.
>> Right there.
Let it up, let it up.
>> PROBST: Chapera with their
boat up.
Mogo Mogo has their boat up.
>> Come on!
>> Push!
>> PROBST: Chapera catching up.
Saboga already bailing.
( indistinct voices )
>> Pick it up, pick it up!
Just bail, just bail.
>> PROBST: Saboga bailing water.
Chapera starting to flip their
boat.
Mogo Mogo almost back to the
platform.
Saboga still bailing water.
Chapera trying to flip their
boat.
Chapera, Mogo Mogo trying to get
their boat flipped.
( indistinct voices )
Chapera flipping their boat.
Chapera's boat is empty.
Mogo Mogo working on flipping
that boat.
Saboga still bailing water.
>> Get out of the boat!
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo's flipped
their boat.
Chapera takes the lead.
( shouting )
Mogo Mogo trying to bail water.
Saboga trying to bail water.
Saboga lost a bailing bucket.
>> Okay, we got it.
One, two...
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo paddling
while they bail.
A risky strategy.
Saboga was the first tribe back
to the platform.
They are still at the platform.
Saboga forgets a paddle, another
mistake.
>> Rudy, get in the boat!
>> Rupert!
>> It's sinking! Bail!
>> PROBST: Hatch takes a dump.
>> Bail in the back, bail in the
back!
>> CHAPERA: One, two, row!
>> Damn it.
>> Team, let's go!
Rudy, get your butt up here!
Where is he?
>> PROBST: Chapera with a big
lead.
>> CHAPERA: One, two.
( grunting )
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo sinking
deeper.
Saboga, you still have a shot.
The first two tribes win
immunity.
>> Everybody out.
Everybody out. Everybody out.
>> PROBST: Chapera first to the
beach.
>> Come on, we can do it.
( cheering )
>> Say it, Jeff, say it!
"Chapera."
>> Whoo!
>> Drop that puppy!
>> PROBST: Chapera, first to
cross, wins immunity.
( cheering )
It is a race for second place.
>> Come on, Mogo Mogo.
We're still in the hunt.
( yelling )
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo wins
immunity.
>> Yeah, baby! Whoo!
>> PROBST: For the second
straight time, Saboga going to
Tribal Council.
Chapera, congratulations.
Immunity...
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: ...once again.
Safe from Tribal Council,
three more days out in Panama.
>> Put it up, let's go!
Whoo!
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo, who wants
it?
Safe from Tribal Council three
more days out in Panama.
What's to say, Saboga?
Great effort, another tough
challenge, another visit to
Tribal Council.
Another tribe member going home.
I'll see you there.
You guys can head back to camp.
>> We had it.
>> We played stronger, we
just didn't play smarter.
>> I was so frantic.
I wanted to get going already.
>> I know.
Then once you and Jerri climbed
in, it was sunk again.
And we had to lift it back up.
It was just a stupid mistake.
>> One stupid mistake.
>> Today's immunity
challenge was a huge letdown,
and each one of us is blaming
ourselves for some part of what
happened.
>> Ethan gets way too
excited at challenges.
This time, even though he helped
so much at the beginning, he
hurt us at the end of the
challenge, and he knew it.
Are you going to see if you can
catch fish?
>> Well, tonight we got
to go to Tribal Council.
And based on last Tribal
Council, you know, I'm going to
go tonight.
And it's scary, you know.
I'm in limbo.
I'm hanging on by a thread right
now.
I got to make sure people want
me here, so why not try to start
spear fishing?
However, if they or we expect to
win any more challenges, you
know, Rudy has to go home.
>> Rudy came to me.
>> Rudy what?
>> Listen to me.
Then we all have to vote for
him.
Are you okay with that?
( sighs )
I hear you.
>> Rudy is most definitely a
hero... more so than any other
person here.
He deserves to be here.
75 years old and doing ( blip )
I can't?
( voice breaking ): It's
killing me to be here.
Rudy came to me on the first day
saying, "I need a buddy."
>> I know what you're
saying.
I adore him.
But we're losing bad.
>> Even though, right now,
discussion is about voting off
Rudy 'cause he's our weakest
link, he's tough as nails.
He never once complained about
anything out here, not once.
>> I don't want to
write anybody's name down.
I'd write my own ( blip ) name
down.
>> Do you want to vote
for Ethan?
>> I'm not writing
Rudy's name down.
I know that.
I'm not writing Rudy's name
down.
>> Bounces off.
>> Bounces off of them?
Probably a good-sized fish, too.
>> Yeah, they're, like,
that big.
>> Yeah.
>> Ethan was out there
by the rocks trying his new
spear, and he came up
empty-handed.
I think Ethan was trying to make
himself more of an asset to the
team, and if he could get fish
as well as Rupert, it would be
harder to vote him off.
And then Rupert walks out into
the water, and it's amazing.
A fish?!
>> We got our first one.
>> Well done.
>> We're having fish
tonight.
>> Damn straight.
>> Oh, my God.
>> He's little, but he's
got some meat.
Oh-ho...!
>> Wow!
>> Now, Rupert goes out.
Five minutes later, he comes
back with a fish.
Great.
>> Come here, Ethan.
Dig in there.
>> Wow, that's yummy.
>> That ain't a bad fish,
you know?
>> Love trigger.
He's a great fish.
>> You know, I'm struggling
out here.
I'm trying to find my niche, and
it's not working.
>> PROBST: So, Rupert, how has
fire improved life at camp?
>> Last time we were here,
we were... sad, we were whipped.
Three days with no food and
water.
Day four came, we won the
challenge, we gave everybody
fire.
We were the victors.
Whew! It was a great day.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's challenge.
From where I was watching, I was
trying to figure out who was
going to come in second, because
Saboga clearly had it won.
And then, Ethan, what happened?
>> Well, we made a silly
mistake.
Instead of pulling the boat up
entirely out of the water and
dumping it, we tried to bail it
while it was still full.
>> PROBST: Jerri, did today's
loss set you guys back in terms
of, now you're going to be down
to four after tonight?
>> Absolutely.
It's our second time in a row
here, and that always sucks.
It just sucks coming here,
period.
>> PROBST: How about you, Rudy?
What is it about this game that
continues to appeal to you?
You've survived situations much
worse than this.
>> I really don't know why
I'm here again.
( chuckles )
I'm three years slower, that's
for sure.
But I like it.
You know, putting up with the
people is the survival part, not
putting up with the elements.
>> PROBST: How are you hanging
in there physically?
>> Good.
I got a sore ankle, but I think
it's going away.
>> PROBST: Rupert, new guy on
the block, but obviously, you
could be odd man out.
>> Oh, yes.
I'm always going to feel that
odd man out.
Um, my one saving grace right
now, I caught a fish.
I caught a fish.
( laughter )
I poked it with a stick.
I caught a fish.
>> PROBST: Rupert starts
catching fish, he becomes much
more valuable. Ethan?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Did you have any
reaction when Rupert came in
with the fish?
>> I was psyched that I
was going to eat.
( laughter )
I mean, yeah, I didn't catch a
fish first, but it doesn't mean
I'm not going to catch ten
tomorrow.
>> PROBST: Ethan, it appeared
last time that Tina was voted
out, if for no other reason than
she's won this game before, and
nobody wanted her to win again.
The only other guy on this block
tonight that's won this game is
you.
So how are you feeling?
>> I feel nervous.
Tribal Council's a scary place.
My insides are upside down,
flipping around, just like that
fish we caught today.
I have a target on my back, and
it's out there in the open.
>> PROBST: So how do you vote
tonight?
Jenna, is there a chance
that it's still a money issue?
>> Yeah, there's still
a chance.
People are voted out of this
game all the time for being too
strong, too alpha male, too much
of a provider.
What's the difference?
Those people don't deserve to
go.
They're providing for their
tribes, but people see them as
competition.
The winners have already won.
That's a strong competition.
So it's just like any other way
to vote, if you see it that way.
>> PROBST: Okay, it's time to
vote.
Jerri, you're up.
>> Rudy, it was an honor to be
on your team, but this is
purely strategical.
>> Ethan, you're tough.
Rudy and I made a pact, and I am
not voting for Rudy.
I got to vote for you, Ethan.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote... Rudy.
Ethan.
One vote Ethan, one vote Rudy.
Two votes Ethan, one vote Rudy.
Rudy.
Two votes Rudy, two votes Ethan.
I'll read the last vote.
Second person voted out of the
Saboga Tribe... Rudy.
You need to bring me your torch.
Rudy, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, Tribal Council is an
interesting place, always
emotional.
Tonight was no exception.
How could you not like Rudy?
75-year-old former Navy SEAL,
hanging with kids a third of his
age: a hero in anybody's book.
I know you didn't want to vote
him out, and yet somebody had to
go, which is exactly what makes
Survivor what it is:
complicated.
Grab your torches, head on back
to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
Rupert and Jerri go
head-to-head.
>> I know what I did,
'cause I've done my ...
for years.
>> Rupert's a complete
control freak.
Let's just ... do it.
>> Jerri and Rupert got
in a fight. Perfect.
That's just what I wanted.
>> PROBST: While Richard faces
off with a shark.
>> Screw it-- I'm not leaving
the thing there, I'm going home
with food.
>> I talked to these people
about two hours ago, and
everything was all set up to
vote Ethan off.
And, uh, I can see Ethan voting
against me, but I can't see the
other two people voting against
me, and if I was them, I'd stay
clear of me.
I got a lot of friends.
That's about all I got to say.