>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Merge was on everyone's mind
when the tribes received body
paint with tree mail.
>> If I was a betting
woman, and I was in Las Vegas,
I'd say we're merging.
>> PROBST: But the merge
never materialized.
Reach in and pick a buff.
You're now a member of Chapera.
Instead, everybody drew buffs to
randomly mix up the tribes.
What, did you think we were
merging?
Just switching things up.
Against all odds, the tribes
stayed intact, merely changing
names, with one exception.
Amber-- the only one to change
tribes.
>> I definitely feel like
I'm the only one who got screwed
in this whole situation.
>> PROBST: The new Chapera tribe
lived it up at their new beach.
>> I realized immediately
that we were so much better off
over here.
>> PROBST: But the new Mogo Mogo
tribe felt their new home was
less that adequate.
>> It's a crap camp.
>> PROBST: While his tribemates
missed their old camp, Rob just
missed Amber.
>> It kills me to have
her over there by herself.
>> PROBST: The Immunity
Challenge tested the tribe's
knowledge of Survivor history.
Mogo Mogo is right.
You win immunity.
And, in a bold move, Boston Rob
offered Lex a deal if he would
save Amber.
Before Tribal Council, Amber was
aware she was the obvious
target, and tried to turn the
heat on Jerri.
>> Please, Kathy, keep me
in the game.
Vote for Jerri.
>> PROBST: And Jerri went after
Amber, the outsider.
>> Boston Rob will tell
you anything to keep Amber
around.
>> This is when the game
changes, when you have to start
making really hard decisions.
>> PROBST: And, at Tribal
Council, Lex and Kathy took a
gamble on Rob's future loyalty,
and voted Jerri out of the game.
Jerri, the tribe has spoken.
Nine all-stars are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Getting rid of Jerri
last night at Tribal Council was
horrible.
I cut her loose to keep Amber
around as a favor to Rob.
When I need to cash in with Rob,
I'm sure he'll deliver.
He's good on his word.
>> We think that Amber's gone,
and it was a very somber mood
around camp.
Rob is really sad.
That was not only his strong
alliance, but, I mean, they're
really dating out here.
>> I hope Amber is still here.
I said some prayers last night
and this morning.
Not much I can do about it.
Maybe Lex came through for me,
and that would be great. Ahh!
>> I've never seen Rob
all screwed up like this, but
it's like when a calf's sucking
its mama's titty and, when you
wean that calf, it bawls, and
it'll go crazy.
It tries to go through fences
and bushes...
Rob's the same way.
And it'll take about three days
to get a calf weaned from its
mother.
A human is about the same.
>> This situation throws
you into a weird kind of arena
where you never know who is
going to be your ally.
You may think one person is
perfect to align with, and then,
all of a sudden, you're, like,
what the hell happened, you
know?
>> We can have, like, a
little silent alliance going.
You know, kind of cover your
tracks and be ready.
You know what I mean?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I'll be completely
alone in this game if Amber is
gone.
I can't trust anybody.
I kind of have a mark on my
back, so I got to watch both
shoulders at all times.
>> I promise you right
now.
>> Okay.
>> Here's the thing.
>> If it comes down to it...
>> If we have...
>> I promise you, I will
fight for you.
>> I will never write
your name down.
>> All right.
>> I will never...
>> I promise you.
>> ...write your name down.
>> I will never write
your name down.
>> That's it.
I won't write your name down.
There's no way.
I would never screw you over.
I'm not going to say that.
>> I didn't say that to
anybody in this game, Alicia.
I did not say that to any one
person in this came.
>> Neither did I.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Chapera, come on in!
(Jenna L. squeals)
>> She made it.
>> PROBST: Jerri voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
Remaining tribe members: Kathy,
Shii Ann, Lex and Amber.
>> Hi, guys.
>> Hey.
>> What's up, Kat?
>> PROBST: Okay.
Let's get to today's Reward
Challenge.
Even though you are still two
tribes, it is an individual
Reward Challenge.
Here's how it's going to work.
All nine of you will start out
on the floating platform.
On my go, all nine of you will
dive down and retrieve one of
seven pots.
Two without a pot will be
eliminated.
We'll work our way from nine
tribe members to seven to five
until we are left with only
three.
We'll then move to a final
round.
The three remaining tribe
members must transport a
heavily weighted crate from the
ocean to the shore.
The first person to cross the
finish line with their crate
wins Reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: For the winner, a
helicopter will land immediately
following the challenge, take
you to a resort.
You'll have a nice shower,
you'll have a massage, facial, a
huge feast.
You'll spend the night-- have a
real bed to sleep on.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winner of the challenge will be
allowed to bring two people from
either tribe.
>> That's a biggie.
>> Wow.
>> That's big.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: All right, pick your
spots out, wait for my go.
Here we go, guys.
Nine tribe members looking for
seven pots.
Survivors ready...
Go!
Get that pot and get back here.
First seven move on.
Everybody has a pot except for
Shii Ann and Jenna.
You two are out.
We're now down to seven.
Looking for five pots.
Survivors ready...
Go!
First five move on to the next
round.
Everybody back up with their
pots.
Amber, Kathy are out.
>> Me and Big Tom were
fighting over it.
>> PROBST: We are down to five.
The first three to get a pot
move on to the final round.
Survivors ready...
Go!
We're looking for three pots.
We have our final three.
Boston Rob, Rupert, Lex.
The other six-- you guys-- can
swim on in.
All right!
It is the final round!
First survivor to get their
crate across the finish line
wins Reward.
(Shii Ann whooping)
Survivors ready...
Go!
Boston Rob swimming out,
diving down.
Rupert moving with his crate.
Lex moving with his crate.
Boston Rob still underwater.
Rupert with a bit of a lead.
Rupert's now on his feet.
He's carrying the crate on his
shoulder.
Boston Rob right behind him.
Boston Rob still in it.
So is Lex.
Boston Rob trying to get it up
on his shoulder.
It's too heavy.
>> Go! Go!
>> Rupert, he's coming!
Come on, Rupert!
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: It's a race to the
finish.
Got to cross the line.
Lex falls down.
(Jenna L. screaming)
Rupert wins Reward!
>> Way to go, Robbo!
>> PROBST: Rupert, get over
here.
Nice job.
>> Won one.
>> Nice job, Rupert.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Okay, big decision.
You can take two people with you
on this Reward.
It can be any two people you
want.
Who's going with you?
>> I honestly wish
everybody could come, I do, but
Amber, you can make up for
that 24 hours you just spent
away from us.
You're coming back.
>> Thank you!
>> It was a hard one, I
know, being away.
>> Nice.
>> Jenna.
We spent the whole time
together.
The first Reward we win, we
share it.
(cheering)
>> PROBST: All right, Rupert,
Jenna, Amber, helicopter's
coming in.
>> Chocolate for me, please.
Double chocolate.
>> Great.
(Rupert chuckling)
>> How come I get so
emotional up here?
>> Ahh! This is so great.
>> My baby is going to say,
"That's my daddy.
He is the toughest daddy in the
world."
>> Oh, my gosh, you guys,
look where we're landing.
Holy crap!
In the middle of this?
>> Oh, my God, that's awesome.
I'm so excited.
Yeah, dinner, showers, massages,
facials and sleep on a bed!
>> I'm in heaven with
two goddesses.
(all laughing)
>> Oh, my God!
(gasps)
>> Look at the shoes!
>> And we get to keep
them, the shoes?
>> I hope so.
>> I have not had a reward
ever in my Survivor history.
>> These are so fun.
>> And I took two
gorgeous girls.
What is this?
>> It's a skirt.
>> I want to wear this home.
It was a great reward.
>> There's deodorant...
Oh, my God, Amber, they have
deodorant.
(women squealing)
Motorized toothbrushes...
>> Mine is blue.
>> Oh, my gosh, smell the
deodorant.
Oh, my gosh, smell yours.
You get your own.
>> Oh, please let us be
able to take these home.
(squeals)
No way!
Makeup.
>> Oh, shut up!
We can paint our toenails?
We're going to get pretty for
you tonight.
>> Beautiful.
>> Oh, my God, what do you do
first?
Strip all those dirty clothes
off, put on the terry cloth robe
and then take a 20-minute shower
using every different sponge
available.
(water running)
>> Could you hand me
that bar of soap?
I'm taking another shower in the
morning.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Do you do the deep
moisturizing treatment frizz
down before conditioner or
after?
>> Before.
>> Before? Thank you.
>> I've never felt so girly.
We each get our own Fantastic
Lash.
That's the kind I use at home,
Aqua Smooth.
>> Really?
>> Mm-hmm. I wanted to paint my
toenails, I wanted to smell
good, I wanted to be pretty.
>> My lips haven't felt
this smooth for so long.
>> I'm the least girly
girl ever.
I've never even had a massage or
a facial, but after 25 days of
not caring it felt good to care.
>> Just feels so good.
>> I'm going to go back
there Superman.
(chuckling)
I can do the last 13 days
standing on my head.
♪ ♪
>> I sat down to dinner
with Amber and Jenna who were
dolled up to the nines,
beautiful lips.
I wanted to kiss and hug 'em all
over.
>> To being clean and
feeling brand-new.
>> Brand-new.
>> Oh, my God, energized
and ready for 13 days.
No matter how it turns out, when
we get home, I have wholehearted
faith in Amber and Rob and Jenna
and Big Tom and I.
Five strong, solid...
>> And we have this.
I really strongly believe we
have this.
>> I think so.
We have a five-way strong no
matter what happens.
>> ...happens. We do.
>> I was a little nervous
because I made a deal with Lex
and Kathy that they could come
to the end with me, Big Tom and
Rob.
But I couldn't tell Rupert and
Jenna that.
>> We'll be the powerhouse.
>> Cheers to that.
>> I know, my God.
(chuckling)
It's very good, very good.
>> We've got mail.
Uh-oh.
"Rise and shine.
It's a good day for competing.
If your survival skills aren't
sharp, you may take a beating.
Make camp life more comfortable,
put the horse before the cart.
If you don't take your time, it
could be over before it starts."
>> Survivor skills.
>> Don't make sense.
Never ever in Survivor, they had
two rewards back-to-back.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Hello.
>> Hey, how is it going
Jeff Pro-Bodine?
>> PROBST: Now bring in the
chopper... Rupert, Amber, Jenna,
returning from their reward.
>> We missed you.
We missed ya.
(helicopter whirring)
>> PROBST: Welcome back...
Rupert, Jenna, Amber.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Amber, looks like you
got your nails done.
>> I did.
>> PROBST: All right.
First things first, Boston
Rob...
I will take back immunity.
A couple of you may realize
we are on the former Saboga
tribe's beach.
That's because the game is about
to change again.
Drop your buffs.
>> Here we go.
>> Here we go again.
(sighs)
>> PROBST: It is time once again
for new buffs.
>> I hope it's a new color
we see coming out of there.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob.
>> No green, no red.
>> PROBST: This time the buff...
(cheering)
it is the merge color.
(Rupert laughing)
>> Try it on.
(cheering and laughing)
>> We love this.
>> This is a great color.
Didn't like that green.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: All right.
Here's how the merge is going to
work.
You will not be returning to
Chapera.
Mogo Mogo.
You will live your remaining
days right here on Saboga beach.
The beach is a little different
from when you last left it,
Rupert and Jenna.
Strong tides, heavy storms
pretty much wiped away your
shelter.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: The timber's still
here.
Your toolbox is still here.
You've got plenty of nails and
rope and wire.
Some of your pots are scattered
around here.
You're going to have to
scavenge, you're gonna have to
find this stuff, but you can
build shelter again.
You've got Boston Rob who's
proven he knows what he's doing.
And because you guys have shown
that you can survive out here 26
days, we figure you do deserve a
little bit of a housewarming
gift.
In keeping with Survivor:
All-Stars...
>> Oh...! What?
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: We have a few items
to help you out with your new
camp.
>> And a canvas.
>> PROBST: Two Hawaiian slings
and a tarp to help keep you dry,
paints for your new tribe flag.
You'll need to come up a new
tribe name.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: The day is already
half over.
Storms can come in at any time.
This is your new home.
Get to work.
>> Yes!
♪ ♪
>> We have Chapera, Mogo
Mogo and Saboga.
>> Right.
So how about...
>> Sapera Mogo.
I kind of like Bogamopera.
Boga... mo... pera.
>> Hey, you guys?
What do you think of Bogamopera?
That's all of us combined, all
the tribes.
>> It's not bad.
>> How about Chaboga Mogo?
>> Chaboga Mogo...
>> Sounds like a dance.
>> ♪ Chaboga Mogo
Chaboga Mogo ♪
>> Let's do it. I love it!
>> I'm thrilled to be
merged, if for no other reason
just because now the game has
changed up.
This is where it gets exciting
for a game player like me who
just enjoys playing the game of
Survivor.
>> As soon as we merged,
Lex comes running over to me,
"Rob, make me feel comfortable.
Tell me that I'm safe.
Tell me that I'm safe."
I will do everything I can, and
you got other friends in the
game, too. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
>> Yep.
>> I'm making the deal,
"Save Amber and I'm going to
help you later on."
You guys didn't really believe
that, did you?
Come on!
>> If I get a sense that,
you know, I'm going to end up
getting, you know, double-
crossed, get a knife in my back
next Tribal Council, I certainly
won't be happy about that.
>> I won't stick a knife in
your back, man.
I ain't gonna do that.
>> All right.
>> I haven't played that
way this time around at all.
I've been playing the game since
the second I got here.
It's all a game, everything.
Make no mistake about it, I am
playing the game.
When I saw you come out of that
challenge, I was, like, so happy
when I seen you, man.
I was so happy.
Listen, this is the way it has
to go down-- we need to get rid
of Lex tomorrow.
>> Why not Jenna or
Rupert first?
I'm here because of him.
>> Don't go soft on me.
I know it sucks.
I promised him the same thing.
He came up to me, first person
he came up to.
>> It's not even that.
It's not that... I'm just...
I don't know, I'm scared.
>> Don't be scared.
>> What if they're
targeting us?
You and I are stirring all this
up.
Do you know what I mean?
There's too many plans floating
around and too many people are
talking.
They're going to realize that
it's all coming down to us very
soon and then they are going to
get rid of us instead of getting
rid of somebody else.
>> It's not coming down to
us because as soon as Lex is
gone, Big Tom doesn't have a leg
to stand on.
I mean, this is a game, Amber.
We're playing for a million
bucks over here, you know?
Like, let me tell you something,
Jenna and Rupert and Big Tom,
they're all gonna try to stick
it in our backs, too, all right?
>> We've got our work cut
out for us because we have so
many deals going along with so
many people.
We have deals with Lex and
Kathy.
We have deals with Rupert and
Jenna.
We have a deal with Big Tom.
Who the hell knows what's going
on with Alicia?
It's insane.
My mind is like, freaking out
right now.
>> Yeah, I definitely
missed you.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right.
Let's get to today's first
individual immunity challenge.
Tribal immunity is no more.
This is what you covet.
>> Wow. That's cool.
>> PROBST: As long as you are
wearing the immunity necklace,
you are safe from the vote at
Tribal Council.
When you don't have this on, you
are vulnerable, and now that
we are in an individual game, it
becomes all that much more
important.
Today's immunity challenge will
test your skills in the water.
First round is a traditional
hold-your-breath competition.
You will be divided into groups
of men and women: The two men
who stay down the longest will
move on to the final round;
the two women who stay down the
longest will move on to the
final round.
For the final round, you will
race along a ladder, which is
tethered to the ocean floor.
Along the way, you'll be
releasing a series of buoys.
The first person to release all
ten buoys wins immunity.
Here's the twist.
We will run the final leg twice.
Two men will run the final leg.
The winner receives immunity.
Two women will run the final
leg.
The winner receives immunity.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: So at tonight's
Tribal Council, two people...
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: ...will be wearing
the necklace.
Two people will be safe from the
vote.
>> That's big.
>> PROBST: I know at this point
in the game-- huge stakes.
>> That's huge.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Swim out.
Wait for my go.
All right, guys. Here we go.
The two women that stay down the
longest and the two men to stay
down the longest move on to the
final round.
Three, two, one, go down.
Alicia and Jenna are up.
First three women are up.
Amber and Kathy are moving on.
Rupert can't hang on any longer,
Rob, Tom and Lex still fighting
for the final two.
Big Tom's out.
Lex and Boston Rob moving on to
the final.
Kathy and Amber moving on to the
final.
All right.
First woman to release all ten
buoys wins immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Kathy and Amber both have their
first buoys up.
Dead even at two.
3-3.
They're dead even at four buoys
each.
Amber with her fifth.
Amber with a slight lead.
One buoy.
Amber with her sixth buoy.
Kathy with her fifth.
Amber leads six buoys-five.
Kathy still struggling.
Get a breath.
Kathy, you're still in it.
>> I can't get the knot.
>> PROBST: Fatigue starting
to set in.
Kathy with her sixth buoy.
We're tied up 6-6.
Kathy takes the lead now 7-6.
Kathy with eight buoys now.
Kathy continues to fight with
nine buoys.
One left, Kathy.
Amber with her seventh buoy.
Kathy with a 9-7 lead.
(Kathy belches)
>> This challenge sucks.
>> PROBST: Let's go, Amber, get
down and get a buoy.
There it is!
Kathy has her tenth buoy and the
flag.
Kathy wins immunity!
Incredible effort.
(cheering)
Here we go.
Kathy already has immunity.
We are looking for a second
immunity winner.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
>> We're tied up at five.
Both guys are up.
Tied up at five.
Lex back down, Boston Rob
getting his breath.
Lex has a lead, 7-6.
Lex pulling ahead, eight buoys
to six.
Boston Rob with his seventh.
Lex with a one-buoy lead, 8-7.
Lex with his ninth buoy.
Boston Rob with his eighth.
Lex is one buoy away.
Boston Rob ties it up.
We're 9-9.
We are dead even, one buoy left.
Lex can't get it.
Still struggling.
Boston Rob down a long time.
He's got it!
Boston Rob comes from behind,
wins immunity!
Hell of an effort, guys.
Congratulations.
Nice job.
>> Thank you.
You are safe at the vote
tonight.
Nice effort.
Safe at the vote tonight.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> PROBST: For the first time,
guys, two people will be safe at
tonight's Tribal Council.
Everyone else is vulnerable.
See you at Tribal.
>> There's something very
telling about the fact that
we've been here now together
merged for a whole day and
there's been absolutely-- he
hasn't lifted a finger to make
us feel comfortable.
>> No, he's pulling our chain.
>> Yeah, he's yanking on our
chain.
>> I know, and I'm so
discouraged by it.
>> I realize that I made a huge
mistake.
I made a potentially game-ending
blunder in agreeing to keep
Amber and get rid of Jerri, and
I think I may be about to pay
for it.
>> I just want to let you
know that I appreciate
everything you did to save
Amber, but myself, Amber, Big
Tom, Jenna, Alicia and, uh...
>> Rupert.
>> ...Rupert have agreed to
stay together as a group.
>> I can't even believe
what I'm hearing.
>> I know.
>> Let me tell you
something right now.
That was not a game or strategy
decision.
>> It was a strategy decision.
You have nothing to be angry
about.
>> It was a brother coming
to another brother saying friend
to friend, and you know what, I
had my game all worked out, and
if I had gotten rid of Amber,
you know what I would have come
in here with?
I would have come in here with
my numbers advantage and I did
that just because you're my
friend.
>> In fact, I-I-I
completely... my own game.
I screwed my own game up.
>> I'm sorry, buddy.
>> I just can't believe
what I'm hearing.
>> You're asking me to
screw everybody else now for
you.
>> You've got more
allegiance to them than you've
got to me... after asking me for
a special friend favor.
>> I made an agreement with
them.
I asked you for a favor.
>> It's about being
betrayed by my friend.
It's about getting a knife in
the back.
>> Like, honestly, I don't know
what you want me to say, Lex.
I know, like...
>> I want you to say that
you're going to be truthful to
the word you gave me.
>> The word I gave you--
make no mistake about it, Lex--
between you and I, and you want
to put our friendship on the
line, I'll put our friendship
on the line over this.
The word I gave you was that if
I can take care of you, I will.
I'm sorry, I cannot.
>> We were always
thinking of bringing you along,
babe-- always, always until the
bitter end.
He was proud to bring you to the
final four.
>> I'm sorry.
>> That's brutal.
>> It is.
>> It's brutal.
>> Brutal.
>> Absolutely brutal.
Man, I should have listened to
you: "No friends in this game."
>> I asked you for a favor
and if there was anything I
could do, Lex, I would.
>> That's just it.
There's a lot you can do.
>> No, the only thing I can
do is to break my word and screw
everybody else.
>> I just, I just don't
understand.
I mean, you're breaking my
heart, I can't...
I can't even believe it.
>> ...and that's why I'm
crying because I actually came
to him.
>> I-I would...
>> I'm sorry you feel that way.
I really, truly am.
I'm really sorry that you feel
that way.
>> Despite the fact that
Boston Rob is a really nice kid,
there's something inside of him
that came out in Marquesas
that's still here.
And it's just so sad.
It's so sad.
>> He put a knife in my back.
>> Yeah.
Well, this is what I'm doing.
I don't want to stay here.
(crying)
>> Sweetie pie, come here.
>> No, I don't want it.
>> Honey...
>> I don't want it.
>> I don't blame you.
>> I don't believe it's
just a game, not when
friendships are involved, so I
would like to give my immunity
to Lex tonight and if I get
voted off, I'm gone.
I mean, my options are to do
that or to come back here
cowering.
I'm giving it to you tonight.
I hate it.
>> No, no, no, no.
>> This isn't worth it.
>> No, no, you earned it.
>> I can go make a
million dollars somewhere.
>> No, no, no, honey. No, no.
>> Look. Look at me.
If Lex got voted out tonight and
Boston Rob got away with it,
uh-uh.
I am not doing that.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Tribal
Council, where, once again,
tonight you must vote somebody
out of this game.
A little different stakes
tonight, though.
The person voted out tonight
will become the first member of
the jury.
So, from this point forward, it
not only matters who you vote
out, but how you vote them out,
because ultimately only two of
you will make it to the final
two.
The other seven will make up the
jury, who will decide who wins
the million dollars.
Having said that, let's get to
the last few days.
Rupert, did the game ratchet up
a notch today?
>> Today when we got
back to our camp, everything was
tested, you know... alliances
were tested, physical endurance
was tested.
Your mental abilities,
everything was tested.
Today was a very hard day.
>> PROBST: So there's more to
the looks of despair and huge
bags than just the physical.
It's the mental part of what is
happening right now in the game.
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Can you get it back?
Is tomorrow another day?
>> Tomorrow is most
definitely another day.
>> Hopefully the sun comes
out tomorrow.
We need the sun.
>> Tomorrow is most
definitely another-- a new day.
As the rain comes...
>> PROBST: As the rain starts to
send you a signal that Mother
Nature may not be on the same
game plan as you.
>> You got two choices,
Jeff, laugh or cry.
>> PROBST: Lex, how much has the
game changed in the last 24
hours, now that it is an
individual game?
>> The game has changed in
a huge way for those of us who
came from Chapera.
For us, life has become much
more of a true game of survival,
a struggle.
It's a different game for us for
sure.
>> PROBST: So it's a long, cold
night with eight people who will
be going back that aren't
necessarily getting along at
this point, fair to say, Jenna?
>> Very fair to say.
There's a lot of arguments,
today, centered around
loyalties, alliances, tribal
voting lines, and who is going
tonight, and game plans are
spoken aloud and it wasn't nice
for anyone to hear.
>> PROBST: Amber, you going to
go back to a camp divided?
>> I think... Yeah.
I think going back to camp
tonight will be very
uncomfortable, um, but it's a
very important vote, a very
important vote.
>> I've got something I
want to say.
I know we're playing a game, but
I know, like, emotions are real
and feelings are real out here,
and regardless of what happens,
I just want everybody to know
that if I'm your friend, I'm
your friend, and after this is
over, you don't want to be my
friend, then I can't do anything
about that...
But friendship is lasting.
>> PROBST: I just want to give
everybody here a hug.
Man, you guys look awful.
All right.
Let's get to the vote.
For the first time ever, we have
two people with immunity, Kathy
and Boston Rob.
As always, if you guys want to
give that immunity up for some
reason, you certainly can.
Boston Rob, you're shaking, is
that a no or just a shiver?
>> I covet this.
>> PROBST: You're not giving it
up.
Kathy, you keeping yours?
>> I thought about it.
I'm keeping it.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Kathy cannot be voted for.
Boston Rob cannot be voted for.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Big Tom, you're up.
>> I'd much rather be
casting this vote for your
little errand boy, but you're
just gonna have to do.
>> Hey, buddy, sorry about the
vote.
Thanks for keeping Amber around.
I hope we can get over this,
man.
(Kathy sighs)
>> Amber, you didn't have
to tell me that Boston Rob and
you were going to bring us to
the final six.
I just don't like getting lied
to that big.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: "Amber."
"Amber."
That's two votes Amber.
"Lex."
That's two votes Lex, two votes
Amber.
That's three votes Lex.
That's four votes Lex.
Tenth person voted out of
Survivor: All-Stars and the
first member of our jury, Lex.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good luck, y'all.
>> PROBST: Lex, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, you've lasted 27 days.
I know it's been a long, wet,
rainy day.
The rain has stopped.
Maybe it's a sign.
Either way, you got to dig deep.
You got 12 days left-- a one-in-
eight shot at a million bucks.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Good night.
(theme song playing)
>> PROBST: Next time
on Survivor: The All-Stars get a
glimpse of home.
Maybe give you what you need to
get you through these last 11
days.
And Kathy stirs things up.
>> Yeah, you should.
I don't want her to win.
>> I see what's happening
right now.
I think they are switching.
>> I think we've got some
last-minute scrambling going on
in Panama today.
>> Wow.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't
disappointed, but I came into
this game the wealthiest man in
the world.
I have an amazing wife, two
beautiful sons, a loving family
and the greatest group of
friends a man could ever hope
for.
Everything above and beyond that
is gravy as far as I'm
concerned.
Big Tom, you get out there and
give 'em hell.
I'll be rooting for you all the
way. Love ya.