>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Rupert tried to prove himself to
his new Chapera Tribe.
>> The role of provider is wide
open here.
>> He can continue to feed me
until it's time for him to go.
And that time will be determined
by me.
>> PROBST: Colby and Shii Ann
clashed over strategy.
>> Someone like you doesn't have
to lie this entire game because
you don't make a decision.
>> Captain America with his good
teeth... blah, blah, blah, blah.
blah.
>> PROBST: At Chapera, Sue
complained to her tribe about
the incident with Richard during
the reward challenge.
>> I hope to God they vote him
off.
>> Right.
>> He does not deserve to be
here.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: At Mogo Mogo, Lex
took a stab with the spear.
>> Sharpshooter.
Should have gotten rid of
Richard a long time ago.
>> I didn't think it was
necessary to let everyone know
that I was an accomplished
fisherman.
>> PROBST: Back at Chapera, a
four-way alliance was born.
>> Rob and I came up with the
idea to approach Rupert and
Jenna.
>> We all have each other's word
that we will stay our support.
>> PROBST: And before the reward
challenge, the tribe coped with
Sue's downward spiral.
>> Sue is either A: looking to
cash in on a huge payday, or Sue
is really emotionally distraught
by the whole thing, or Sue's
using this as some kind of a
leverage to play the game of
Survivor.
Nobody knows what Sue's thinking
except Sue.
>> PROBST: At the challenge, Sue
spoke out and threw in the
towel.
>> I was violated, humiliated,
dehumanized and totally spent,
Jeff!
And I'm done with the game!
>> PROBST: Sue's sudden
departure from the game left the
tribes with a tough decision.
We continue or we forgo the
reward.
You guys can sit down here and
split this up and eat on your
own.
>> We're here to play.
>> We want to play.
>> PROBST: Go!
Both tribes moved forward and
played for a reward of kabobs.
And with that, Mogo Mogo wins
reward!
(cheering)
Back at camp, Mogo Mogo savored
their victory...
>> This is good.
>> I just wanted to rub my face
in it.
>> PROBST: ...and discussed
Sue's decision to quit.
>> I was really offended that
she'd bring us that far into her
core of hatred.
I don't like her for it.
I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: And at Chapera, the
tribe vowed to stick together.
>> We're six strong, they're six
strong.
We should be able to win this if
you think about it.
>> One, two, three, Chapera!
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
(birds singing)
>> See the sky?
>> I know.
It's pretty.
>> (yawns): Oh, my God.
My back is killing me.
>> Ay-yi-yi-yi.
>> Something was biting pretty
bad last night, too.
>> Jerri is starting to drive me
insane.
"I couldn't sleep last night on
the rack.
It was really painful."
Hello?
We all slept on the rack last
night, and, yeah, it was
painful, but your voice was the
only one bitching about it all
night long.
Kathy, I'll go get the water.
I don't mind.
>> You sure?
>> Yeah.
>> Jerri, do you need any of
this water?
>> Yeah.
I haven't been drinking enough.
>> Jerri doesn't really have a
huge work ethic and when you
got a bad seed in the team,
man, it brings it down, and I
don't even mean a bad seed as
much as just an annoying seed.
So that's grating on people, and
I know it drives Colby up the
ying-yang.
>> Jerri has not changed one
iota from the first time she
played this game.
Her game play hasn't changed,
her attitude, the way she treats
other people, none of that has
changed, but I really let it
just roll off my back, and maybe
it's because I know Jerri's not
going to win this game.
>> (Southern accent): I swear
that woman is such a bitch.
(both laughing)
I love slam-dunking people.
(laughter continues)
>> I know that I'm pretty much
on my own.
I'm a little stressed out about
it, but I feel pretty
comfortable because I'm
constantly being underestimated,
and that's right where I wanted
to be: the nonthreatening, Zen-
like, easygoing Jerri who's here
to have fun.
So I say bring it on.
Let's go.
Game on.
>> Open it up.
>> A puzzle.
>> We just got our tree mail for
the day.
It looks like it's going to be
an immunity challenge.
Game on.
>> Game on.
>> It's for reward? Immunity?
>> For Immunity.
>> For immunity?
>> Yep.
>> Wow.
It's a puzzle.
>> It's a puzzle.
>> "Living on the island, you
need the ocean to survive.
Be the first to master the sea,
three more days you'll stay
alive.
Huge consequence if you move too
slow.
Be the last to finish, you may
be the next to go."
It sounds like it's individual.
>> It is, yeah, it does.
>> Could be teams still.
>> The merge is coming, I feel
it, and knowing that now we're
even numbers with the other
tribe, we want to kind of get
somebody under our wing, maybe,
to have those high advantage in
numbers.
>> We're not losing.
>> Especially a swimming
challenge.
We've got them whupped on a
swimming challenge.
If Ethan now is their best
diver, oh, my God, we've got
them whupped hands down.
>> Yeah, he freaks out during
challenges.
He's strong, but he freaks out.
>> He gets panicked.
My goal before our challenge was
to pound that into them, even if
we get behind, we stay calm, we
stay focused, and we try hard.
We'll win, guaranteed, if we
keep our composure and we try
hard.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
What's going on, Mogo Mogo?
>> Hey, Jeff.
>> PROBST: What's up, Chapera?
>> What's going on, Jeff?
>> PROBST: Okay, for today's
challenge, each tribe will start
on a floating platform.
One at a time, tribe members
will swim out to retrieve
floating puzzle pieces.
Once you have all the pieces,
you can begin assembling the
puzzle.
When it's completed, it will
form a giant floating puzzle
boat.
You'll use braces to secure the
boat, take the four paddles,
paddle into shore, at which
point, one tribe member will
race into the jungle to the
giant palm tree, cut a rope,
releasing a tribe flag and two
more paddles.
It's then a race back to the
starting platform.
First tribe to get back with all
six paddles, their boat and all
six tribe members wins.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For the winning
tribe, a chance to get off the
island for the entire day and
enjoy a nice, big ol' fat
barbecue.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Juicy burgers, hot
dogs, French fries.
In addition, nice selection of
desserts.
(all gasp)
>> PROBST: And it wouldn't be a
barbecue without what?
>> Beer!
Yeah!
(applause)
>> PROBST: I'll do you one
better than beer-- open bar.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
In addition to being a reward
challenge, it is also an
immunity challenge.
That means winning tribe also
has immunity.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Losing tribe, Tribal
Council tonight.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Somebody voted out.
Now worth playing for?
(all agreeing)
>> PROBST: One more twist.
The winning tribe will select
one member from the losing tribe
to join them on the reward,
which means they partake in the
barbecue and they avoid Tribal
Council.
They cannot be voted out.
Could be an offensive move,
could be a defensive move,
could be a chance to get
information about the other
tribe.
Because this challenge is for
such high stakes, it's going to
be tough.
Give you a couple of minutes to
strategize.
We'll get started.
Here we go, guys.
For reward and immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Go, Rob.
Boston Rob uses the boat for a
launch.
Jerri in for Mogo Mogo.
Boston Rob dives down.
Jerri dives down.
Rob has his first piece for
Chapera.
Jerri struggling for Mogo Mogo.
Jerri has the first piece for
Mogo Mogo.
Got to hit the dock then the
next person can go.
>> Swim!
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Big Tom in for
Chapera.
Big ol' splash.
Jerri trying to get back.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Big Tom with another
piece for Chapera.
Shii Ann swimming out for Mogo
Mogo.
Shii Ann coming back with a
second piece for Mogo Mogo.
>> Come on, Shii Ann, push!
>> PROBST: Alicia goes down for
Chapera.
Colby in the water for Mogo
Mogo.
Alicia has the third piece for
Chapera.
>> Push it, push it!
>> PROBST: Colby trying to make
up some ground for Mogo Mogo.
Donaldson is unhooked and
heading back.
Mogo Mogo making up a lot of
ground.
Rupert in the water for Chapera.
>> Come on, Rupert!
>> PROBST: Kathy in the water
for Mogo Mogo.
>> Go, Kathy!
>> PROBST: Chapera still in the
lead, but Kathy making up a lot
of ground for Mogo Mogo.
Jenna in the water for Chapera.
>> Come on, Jenna!
Go for it!
>> PROBST: Jenna having trouble
getting her piece untethered.
Ethan in the water for Mogo
Mogo.
Jenna has the fifth piece
unhooked and is heading back.
Ethan heading back for Mogo
Mogo.
It's very tight.
>> Go!
Amber in the water.
Ethan still heading back for
Mogo Mogo.
Go!
Lex for Mogo Mogo.
It's a race to get the last
piece.
Amber is untied and heading
back.
>> Come on, Amber!
>> PROBST: Lex on her tail.
Lex heading back for Mogo Mogo,
Amber heading back for Chapera.
Once she hits the dock, you can
start putting the puzzle
together.
Go!
Chapera starts to put their boat
together.
Lex has to get back.
Start putting it together, Mogo
Mogo.
Both tribes working on their
boat.
Ethan and Colby with the first
two pieces for Mogo Mogo.
Mogo's plan is working.
Pieces are falling in nicely.
Lex has the last piece of the
puzzle for Mogo Mogo.
Mogo Mogo has their boat
together.
Put in the slats.
Chapera had a lead, but they've
lost it.
>> Give me a slat!
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo working
together patiently.
Once you feel your boat's
secure, head out.
Ethan tries to use the paddle
and breaks it.
Mogo Mogo heading out.
With all their braces in place
their boat is sturdy, secure.
They have three paddles.
Boston Rob wants Chapera to head
out.
The boat is not quite together.
It's a tight race.
Mogo Mogo with a bit of a lead.
Got to hit your poles, guys.
Mogo Mogo hits the pole.
Ethan is off heading into the
jungle.
Chapera's close behind.
Got to hit the pole.
>> Go.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob in the
water heading into the jungle.
Ethan with a big lead for Mogo
Mogo.
Mogo Mogo's raised their flag.
Chapera has raised their flag.
>> Come on, Rob!
>> Rob!
>> PROBST: Boston Rob has passed
Ethan, made up a lot of ground.
>> Come on, Rob!
>> PROBST: It's going to come
down to paddling-- which tribe
can work together.
>> Stroke!
Stroke!
>> PROBST: Reward and immunity
at stake.
Mogo Mogo with a slight lead
now, making up ground in the
water.
We're neck and neck.
Mogo Mogo off-course now.
Trying to correct.
Chapera heading straight for
their dock.
Mogo Mogo just lost a lot of
ground.
Chapera now with the lead.
Mogo Mogo struggling with the
paddling.
Chapera straight and narrow,
heading right for their dock.
Chapera wins reward and
immunity!
>> Chapera!
>> PROBST: Chapera, immunity.
(tribe cheering)
You also have a big reward:
barbecue, dessert, open bar,
and a big decision.
Which member of Mogo Mogo are
you taking with you, and which
member are you going to keep
from Tribal Council tonight?
Give me a decision.
>> We'll take Kathy O'Brien.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Kathy!
You've been selected to come
over with Chapera.
Good news, bad news.
Mogo Mogo, unfortunately, for
you guys, Tribal Council
tonight.
There's somebody going home and
it's not going to be Kathy.
I'll see you there.
Chapera, by the way, that's your
ride, a 94-foot luxury yacht.
(tribe shrieking)
(whooping)
(excited chattering)
>> When the other tribe
picked me to go with them on the
reward, my head just bowed.
I mean, I just didn't want to
go-- I thought it looked bad.
>> Oh, yippee, baby!
>> I also was really crushed
that we lost.
>> Oh, my God.
>> My hands are shaking.
>> And yet, just getting
to go to the multimillion dollar
yacht was a treat.
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
>> You're welcome, Kathy.
Have fun.
>> Enjoy.
>> Oh, my God...
>> And you...
>> You have good friends on this
tribe.
(whooping)
>> To teamwork!
>> Three more days!
>> Yeah!
(shouting happily)
>> That boat, I ain't ever
seen a boat like that.
It reminded me of the fanciest
house trailer you ever seen...
float.
It's a house.
It's a house on a lake.
It was the only one I've ever
been on, but I know I couldn't
have picked a nicer one.
>> Food is ready!
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
(Jenna shrieks)
(excited chattering)
>> Some people grabbed plates.
I didn't even grab a plate.
I just started picking at the
food left and right, cheese and
pickles and bread and...
It was so great.
We needed that.
>> There's burgers this
thick and dogs and brats and
lettuce and cucumbers and salad
and asparagus and corn on the
cob and salty, greasy, beautiful
food.
>> Jenna, there's no way you can
eat all that.
>> I'm so puking this up and
eating dessert.
>> Hell, yeah.
>> I totally forgot about
dessert.
>> Yesterday, you're like, you
might have a piece of rice.
>> Do I have something right
here?
>> Do I have snail in
my teeth?
>> I felt totally welcomed
by Chapera.
I mean, they brought me in like
I was one of their tribe
members.
>> It's funny, because every
time you think it can't get
better...
>> It does.
>> ...it does.
>> I feel that there's going to
be a lot of tension for me, if
we do merge, in swinging, you
know, from this loy... this
loyalty to that loyalty, and if
I do, where and when I swing,
I've got to really be careful.
(all singing country tune)
>> ♪ We got a new girl, her
name is Cat ♪
>> ♪ She fits in just like
that
♪ Doo-dah, Doo-dah day
Doo-dah, Doo-dah day
Doo-dah, Doo-dah day... ♪
>> Yeah!
>> Huge, huge challenge today.
Huge reward for the winning
tribe, and unfortunately, for
us, we basically got beat out by
just a hair, and the lead was
ours to lose the whole time.
I mean, I'd be lying if I
said it wasn't an enormous
disappointment-- it was a huge
disappointment.
>> I just want to
apologize formally.
I screwed up, and, uh...
>> I don't think its any one
person's fault, Ethan.
>> Yeah, I think we all tried.
>> I know we all tried,
but I feel responsible and I'm
taking responsibility for it and
I'm sorry.
>> Right on.
>> I feel largely
responsible for our loss today.
I just could not get those ropes
untied, and I lost the lead.
>> You want to talk about it?
>> I couldn't get the knot out.
The knot was tight.
I just couldn't get the knot
out.
You know, my tribe sees me as
a powerhouse, as, you know,
someone who can help them in
challenges, and I failed, and
it feels horrible to fail,
you know.
You're either the hero or you're
the goat, and today I was the
goat.
Do they see a need for me here,
or can they just let me go?
I don't know, and obviously
we've got to vote someone off
tonight.
>> First, we get off the boat
and they take us to this oasis.
It was so inviting, and you know
something's great coming, so
you keep getting more excited.
You just ate a huge meal, you
should be happy, but you know
something more's coming.
>> We're walking up to
something good, guys.
We are definitely...
>> We are in something
good and it just keeps getting
better with every step.
>> Oh...
>> Oh, my God, chocolate.
>> Oh, my God.
>> And there stands a
large cart with every kind of
dessert you can imagine.
Mmm!
(all groaning with pleasure)
I've never packed so much food
in my mouth in a short time.
It was disgusting, but so good.
>> Yeah, that's peanut buttery.
>> Is that cheesecake over
there?
What is that?
>> Oh, my God.
>> I'm going in there.
I mean, it's just too beautiful
to pass up.
>> The water is crystal clear.
>> Crystal clear.
>> You guys should come see
this.
>> The gorgeous waterfall
right below us.
It's just so crazy to think
places that beautiful exist in
the world and...
that the fact
that we're getting a chance to
see them.
(laughs)
>> You guys, this is
unbelievable.
The Chapera tribe-- you know
what they've got that we don't
have, is they're having fun.
They're enjoying the game.
And I knew it was lacking with
my Mogo Mogo tribe.
I wasn't having fun, it's just
been work, work, work.
And yet, Chapera's having a
great time.
I mean, they're dancing, they've
got silly little songs.
When you do go away and you
experience civilization again,
all of a sudden, it opens your
head as to other options.
If I choose to swing over to
them, it's just gonna have to be
the right time and tons of
communication.
It'll be tricky, but there's
no way I'm going to tell my
tribe that I fit in like a
glove.
Mm-mm, no.
>> You'd eat that?
I think it's rotten.
You would?
>> I'd eat that.
>> You would, okay.
>> If you cook it.
>> Okay. I'll cook it.
>> Everyone is on edge.
Regardless of whether people
want to pretend like they're
happy to see each other or if
they're having fun or not, it's
a very stressful situation.
God bless America.
>> That's something
that I'm going to sauté.
Jerri is just rubbing me the
wrong way.
She's only willing to do the
chores that you're already
doing.
>> Shii Ann, if you want,
I'll take that out and you can
chop that up or whatever.
>> No, it's okay.
You can chop it.
I'm just going to chip these
off.
She didn't want to eat the
rotting coconut, and I was going
to put some of the rotting
coconut into the pot to cook and
she snapped at me.
>> Shii Ann...
>> I saw Shii Ann roll
her eyes at Jerri again today.
She's fed up with all of Jerri's
stuff.
She can't wait to vote her off.
>> Okay, well...
>> I say we put the
boxing gloves on.
There's no difference between
Jerri and Shii Ann to me.
I don't care for either one of
them.
Shii Ann annoys me as much if
not more than Jerri does, so if
it came down to tolerance or
personal irritation, I'd have a
tough time deciding.
>> What a beautiful,
beautiful day.
>> ...anything to drink?
>> Yes.
Are you serving alcohol?
(laughing): Oh, my God!
>> I'm having a margarita,
please.
>> I'll have a beer.
>> Beer.
>> Wow.
>> Here we go.
All right.
>> Environmentally friendly golf
balls, so you're free to pick a
club.
>> I'll take that one.
>> I was on the state
championship golf team at my
high school.
>> Hey, you damn ball.
I'm going to beat you.
>> Wow!
>> There goes the driver.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, no.
(laughing)
Oh, my God.
>> Fore!
>> That was the funniest thing
yet.
>> You are just trouble,
you know that?
>> Just every time.
>> Just trouble.
>> Every time.
>> If I catch a fish today,
I beat Rupert.
Just a little bit of luck.
That's all I want to do.
He's beaten me every day, but
today, I'm hoping Big Tom
scores.
>> Kathy...
>> Yeah?
>> Your tribe is probably
leaving right now for Tribal
Council.
>> I know they are.
They are running around trying
to figure out what to do, too.
>> Kathy is a tough
woman, and wants to get as far
as she can in this game, and she
may be the perfect person to try
to pull over into our group.
>> Probably seems like you might
rub Lex anything... normal.
>> Too many chiefs.
>> He's just playing real hard.
>> She offered up a lot
of information.
>> So you and Lex vote
along the same lines.
And what about Shii Ann, where
does she fit in?
>> She's with us.
>> She's with you.
>> We've pretty much
figured that out.
I am not sure that she's telling
us 100% the truth.
I wouldn't expect her to be
telling us the truth, unless she
is foreseeing that her tribe is
one member down, and she's going
to have to save her ass.
>> I had four poles and
never caught a fish.
So Rupert caught more fish in
a day with a stick than I did on
a $3 million yacht.
But I'm going to tell you
something.
Kathy fell in our trap.
We got the girls up there
numbing her up.
I didn't think she'd fall, but
she is, she's up there...
They're getting her numb now.
>> I'm so sorry.
(conversation fading)
>> I'm not feeling good
and I'm not feeling secure about
my position here at all.
You know, I'm at a loss right
now.
I'm all over the place.
I'm a jumbled puzzle.
But I feel there is a way out.
(chuckles)
>> I've been pushing for
Jerri since day one.
She's getting on our nerves.
It was pretty simple to go to
Colby and say "Jerri."
So it was an easy choice.
>> I think our decision was made
when Jerri Manthey came on
board.
I mean, that's the one we want
to get rid of.
And that's just the effect she
has on people.
I don't know that this game is a
game that's meant for Jerri
Manthey to play.
>> You don't get far in
this game by playing safe.
I had already made a conscious
decision to change my strategy
from how I played in Africa, in
that I was going to come in here
and if I had to make hard
decisions, and if I had to do a
little lying, I was going to do
it.
Want to go for a little walk?
>> Hmm?
>> I find myself now at the
doorway of an opportunity to do
just that, for the first time in
the game-- to really do
something that probably no one
is going to expect me to do.
Their plan is to get rid of you
tonight.
>> I knew that was coming.
>> And they think I'm agreeing
with them and that Shii Ann is,
as well, okay?
But that's not going to happen.
We're going to do Colby tonight.
>> I'm very content with
that decision.
>> I've thought about this
a lot, and I think that we're
just... we're on the eve of a
merge, and Colby is so
dangerous, post-merge, when he's
doing individual challenges--
he's dangerous.
>> I mean, that's something you
don't even have to tell me
about.
I already dealt with him...
>> So you're on board.
>> Totally.
>> You, me and Shii Ann
are voting for Colby.
He's not gonna see this coming a
mile away, I don't think.
This is my one and only
opportunity to take him out
before it goes...
slips right through my fingers.
So I'm jumping on it.
>> Well, I am solid on that
vote.
'Cause there's... there's a
tad bit of revenge there, so...
I'm a little nervous.
I'm just hoping that the info
that I'm getting is, in fact,
what's going to happen tonight.
But there's always a chance Lex
could be playing me, just as
much as he's playing Colby.
>> I think he's going to
take it hard, 'cause I don't
think he's going to expect it.
But as far as he knows now, I'm
taking you aside to tell you
that it's Ethan.
>> Colby doesn't see this
coming at all.
He doesn't see a single vote
coming in his direction.
For me, that was a goal, that I
set for myself, was to last
longer than Colby.
And if it took losing today to
get him out of here, I'm totally
fine with it.
>> But I know you're solid.
I'm not worried about it.
Shii Ann, this is the difference
between her lasting a long time
in this game or her going in a
few days.
>> Yeah, okay.
>> I think there's going to
be big surprises tonight.
I think there's a lot of people
that probably won't see it
coming.
I think that for you especially,
right now, this is like a real
cusp moment.
>> I know.
>> And if we...
>> I'm so...
>> ...if we can pull this
off, you are so in there, I am
so in there.
>> I feel trouble
brewing in this camp.
Lex came up to me and asked me
to vote out Colby today.
But Jerri is so lazy, she annoys
me, she doesn't work that much
at camp.
I want to think about nothing
but how to vote you off.
Kathy, my biggest ally, is on a
boat somewhere.
I'm stuck here with a bunch of
power players, and I've got to
make my move.
>> Whee!
(Tom singing gibberish)
>> Big Tom just said,
"I really miss my goats."
(Alicia laughing)
Cut him off.
No more booze for this man.
>> That's it.
>> Oh, we got champagne!
(cheering and whooping)
>> We had come to the end
of a perfect day.
So we went out onto the bow, and
they brought us out champagne.
(cheering)
And the sun was going down.
It was just a perfect, perfect
moment.
>> All right, let's toast.
>> Here's to one of the
most memorable days we'll ever
have probably in our lives.
>> And you know what?
Here's to having a blast at this
game.
(Tom belches)
>> I ain't drunk much champagne,
but I didn't think much of it.
It had too many bubbles in it.
But I ain't gonna be bitching
with my mouth full, don't get me
wrong.
>> I just might have to stay
over here.
>> I'd be lying if I said,
you know, I won't go to Tribal
Council with a certain amount of
fear, but I feel as confident as
I could...
that everything at
this point is going to go
according to plan.
>> Everybody ready?
>> If tonight is played
straightforward, it should be
four votes to one, Jerri Manthey
going home, but as we've all
known from the get-go, it's a
game of curveballs.
If Jerri feels as though her
back's against the wall, who
knows what she could pull out?
That is another reason why she
needs to go tonight.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Tribal
Council.
Let's talk about today's
challenge.
Reward and immunity and access
to one of your tribe members,
which could potentially be
devastating, if they give up
information.
What happened, Ethan?
You guys had a huge lead going
into the jungle.
>> Huge is, you know, a
matter of opinion, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Pretty big.
>> Nah, okay.
No, you're right.
Um, I take full responsibility
for what happened with the
challenge today.
I feel horrible about it.
I feel bad I let my team down,
let myself down, uh, and it's
embarrassing.
I don't want to lose to Rob.
I don't want to lose to Chapera.
>> PROBST: Colby, it seems like
there's a little bit of
animosity between these two
tribes.
>> Yeah.
I agree with Ethan.
I hated losing to Rob.
I don't think any of us are
looking forward to a merge.
Coexisting and cohabitating with
those guys is not something I'm
looking forward to.
>> PROBST: Lex, are you guys
really already thinking about a
merge?
>> All of us are definitely
thinking about a merge.
I mean, every time we go to a
challenge and see these other
players, we're sizing them up.
>> PROBST: So, it stands to
reason, if you're looking at
Chapera and thinking who's
going to be a threat, you must
be looking at your own tribe
already and thinking who's
going to be a threat.
>> You better believe it.
Absolutely.
Who's going to be a threat, and
who's going to be somebody that
can help you...
in a post-merge situation.
>> PROBST: Jerri, so how do you
navigate this one?
Because it's still a tribal
game.
>> When I vote, I vote...
for the person I find to be my
biggest threat, because that
definitely comes into play at a
merge.
That is something that you have
to consider throughout the
entire course of the game.
>> And I disagree with that.
I'm sorry, if you're not
through, I'll let you finish.
>> No, go ahead.
>> We're here because we lost.
We can't afford to lose again.
It doesn't make sense to start
eliminating people that you
know, in some capacity, will
help you compete.
To me, it just doesn't make
sense to start cutting your legs
off.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann, who could
this tribe most afford to lose,
from a physical point of view?
>> Well, from a physical point
of view, it would probably be me
or Jerri.
We're physically possibly the
weakest tribe members here.
I'm sorry, Jerri, to speak for
you...
>> Yeah, please don't.
>> ...but physically I think
we...
But I would hate for this vote
to be purely based on physical
strength, because obviously,
then...
I might be the next to
go, and I would not like to go
at this time.
>> PROBST: Jerri, do you agree
with Shii Ann?
Are you possibly one of the
weakest links on this tribe?
>> Um... well, I'm really good
at putting puzzles together.
(laughs) Um, I'm good at
strategizing.
And I feel like I am an
uplifting member who is
generally in a good mood and
keeping spirits high, and I feel
I have a lot to offer.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann, who could
the tribe least afford to lose
from a physical point of view?
>> Sorry, Ethan, I have to say
that Colby is physically the
strongest member of this tribe.
He's a very valuable member.
Strongest physically, definitely
Colby.
>> PROBST: So, Colby, does that
make you feel secure hearing
that, that you are leading the
tribe?
>> My first thought was,
wow, that really puts me out
there for...
when we do get to
that point where it is
individual.
No offense to you, Shii Ann,
but...
but, yeah, that's weird.
My first thought was, wow, I
don't feel secure now, I feel
vulnerable, because I've just
been pointed out as the
strongest guy in this tribe.
Do they see me as the guy
they've got to get rid of?
>> PROBST: Lex, you think the
person voted out tonight's gonna
be shocked?
>> Tonight, on our tribe,
the only person that doesn't
have to worry about loyalty and
worry about the shock of being
voted out is Kathy, who's
whooping it up with Chapera.
There's gonna be nothing fun
about it.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Ethan, you're up.
>> Jerri...
you're two-faced, so... bye.
>> You and I both know that
this game has absolutely nothing
to do with friendship.
I had to make a hard call and
it meant taking you out.
>> Is this a revenge vote?
Hell, yeah.
>> You have underestimated my
powers.
Perhaps you should spend some
time analyzing your own.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Colby.
That's two votes Colby.
Jerri.
Two votes Colby, one vote Jerri.
Two votes Jerri, two votes
Colby.
I'll read the last vote.
The seventh person voted out of
the tribe...
Colby.
Need to bring me your torch.
Colby, the tribe has spoken.
There you go.
Well, based on tonight's vote,
it seems that the prevailing
wisdom, Mogo Mogo, is to vote
out the person you think will be
most threatening if and when it
becomes an individual game.
Interesting strategy.
We'll see if it pays off or not.
You guys can head back to camp.
Kathy'll be waiting for you when
you get there.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor...
Rob and Amber finally connect.
>> He's getting me
through this game, and I think
I'm getting him through, too.
>> Amber is slammin'.
>> PROBST: Both tribes select
ambassadors.
>> "Pick one representative to
visit Mogo Mogo."
>> That person might have
to stay over there.
>> PROBST: At Chapera, the alpha
males square off.
>> Aqua-Man versus the
city kid from Boston.
>> Tonight was probably
as polar opposite from my first
experience in Survivor.
Every Tribal Council, I was
never voted out.
But the inevitable bonus of
playing this game again is
simply, once again, proving to
yourself that you can do it.
And, ultimately, when your day's
up, you got to be okay with
that.
You got to feel good about what
you've done.