>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor:
After Colby was ousted by Lex's
surprise plan, Jerri celebrated.
(Jerri laughs)
And Ethan, who was told Jerri
was the target, felt betrayed.
>> I made an assumption,
thought everything was going
smoothly and, boom.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, Chapera rolled their
way to victory...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Amber wins the award
for Chapera!
...winning them the right to
loot Mogo Mogo's rice, grill and
fishing spear.
>> I've been waiting 20
days to not have to poke fish
with a stick.
>> PROBST: Late that night, Rob
and Amber finally connected.
>> I love that he, you know,
keeps me warm at night, and he
makes me feel safe out here.
>> PROBST: The following
morning, Rupert realized he
wasn't the sole provider.
>> I'm just glad he
caught a fish.
>> Boston style.
>> Boston Rob.
He's kind of an arrogant pain in
the ass.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Jerri took a gamble
and put Mogo Mogo's fate in her
own hands...
Wide to the right.
Chapera wins immunity.
...and lost.
Back at camp, Jerri was relieved
when Lex told her that Ethan was
the target.
>> I'm just glad it's not me.
>> PROBST: And to avoid
blindsiding his friend from
Africa, Lex told Ethan he was
next to go.
>> It has nothing to do
with friendship.
This is... this is business.
>> PROBST: Ethan scrambled to
stay.
>> Jerri's going to get
further than you and Shii Ann.
>> No.
>> She might.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Ethan was trapped and
couldn't fight his way out.
Ethan.
The last former winner was the
eighth all-star to go.
The tribe has spoken.
Ten all-stars are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(saw cutting wood)
(sawing continues)
>> Timber!
(saw cutting)
>> Tom and I are definitely the
worker bees on Chapera.
I'm not happy for anybody to lay
their ass around in the shelter
and let me do all the work,
but... I can't go in there and
say, "Get your ass out of that
bed and go to work."
I can't say that.
Hopefully, the merge is coming
soon, because once we get
merged, there's other people,
those Mogo Mogo Mogos hopefully
will actually work.
>> Me and Rupert, we get up
early, and the rest of them lays
in, and we go fishing about
every morning.
And if you see that harpoon,
that's the hardest thing to get
that there ever was, 'cause
Rupert been the biggest damn
hog I've ever seen on that
thing.
I've been here 22 days, and I've
yet to touch it, and I ain't
leaving here today till I get in
that water with that harpoon.
I'm gonna catch some fish.
>> You gonna get in the water?
>> Yeah.
>> Right now.
>> I wondered why you
was putting your shoes on.
You're gonna go in the water
with your shoes on?
>> TOM: Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> I'll see you when I catch
one.
>> Okay, good luck.
>> ...might be dark.
>> That's okay.
I'll sit here all day.
>> All right.
>> Bring that whale on in!
Very good, Big Tom, very good.
You are the fisher-man.
Big Tom did get him a little
fish.
Not a bad fish for his first
fish ever on the spear.
That probably hits in the
goldfish category.
That's a fish tank fish.
But Big Tom got it, and he was
thrilled.
>> This rack is wet.
This place sucks.
The weather here, it's wet, all
the time-- just dank, moldy and
wet, all the time.
And it's really, really starting
to take its toll on me.
>> Come on, baby, promise
me you got an ember under there.
Lots of... lots of patience.
Mornings are always tough for
me, just 'cause you wake up and
there's just nothing to burn.
The wet and rain is just too
hard.
There's no dry wood.
It's just, today, not worth it.
And being on a, you know, the
losing team all the time, it's
just depressing.
>> Hey, you guys.
We got some tree mail.
"Today you may improve your way
of life.
It's just a means to the ends.
It may be a battle royal, or you
just might make some friends."
>> Huh.
>> Merge.
>> Yeah.
>> I think it might be a merge.
The tree mail today
came with green paint, which we
don't know what to do with yet.
Either paint each other or paint
something, but it's green.
Mogo Mogo colors, so...
>> I don't know if that's face
paint, so don't put it
it on your face yet.
>> Oh, I wasn't going to.
If I was a betting woman and I
was in Las Vegas, I'd say we're
merging.
>> I can't tell if that's
body paint or not.
I have no idea what the green
paint is about.
I think at this point, rather
than show up looking like a
bunch of, you know, weirdos with
paint, we may just bring the pot
of paint with us.
>> Immediately we take
the body paint and start to
paint each other.
The guys have big bulls on their
chest, and the girls do, like,
dots and arrows and... fun
stuff.
You like that?
>> I love it.
>> We took the paint, and
tick-tock, pokey-pokey,
rubby-rubby.
We was just tickled to death.
(bellows)
>> We know that we're going to
go to the challenge.
We don't know if it's going to
be a merge.
We know something is going to
happen.
>> JEFF: Chapera, come on in!
Looking good.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: I like it.
>> We had fun.
>> We did. Thanks for the paint.
>> PROBST: Mogo Mogo, come on
in.
Chapera getting your first look
at the new Mogo Mogo Tribe.
Ethan voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> Good.
>> PROBST: What's going on, Mogo
Mogo?
>> How's it going, Jeff?
>> Hi.
>> Hey, guys.
>> Looking dandy in the red.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: All right, first
thing I notice, you were both
given a can of paint.
Chapera, what made you guys put
it on your body?
There was no direction.
Rob, is this a sign of team
spirit in a way?
>> Yeah, I guess so.
We're having a good time over
there painting each other.
>> PROBST: At the other end of
the spectrum, why did you guys
decide to do nothing, Kathy?
>> Um, we're just...
we're the civil tribe.
(laughter)
No. We're just, uh... we like to
save things, I guess.
We like to conserve.
>> My canvas is full.
>> PROBST: Okay, here's what I
want to happen.
Mogo Mogo, choose an order, one
through four.
Chapera, choose an order, one
through six, but because you
have two extra people, numbers
five and six will not have a
say.
Huddle up and decide and line up
in order.
Okay, we're gonna alternate
between tribes.
Lex, as number one for Mogo
Mogo, you will start.
Pick one member from Chapera
that you would like to sit down
and have a private conversation
with, separated from everybody
else.
>> I believe I'll take you, Rob.
>> 'Kay.
>> PROBST: All right, Lex and
Rob, over here.
You're the first pair.
Big Tom, pick somebody from Mogo
Mogo.
>> Uh...
I'll take Jerri.
>> PROBST: 'Kay. Jerri and big
Tom gonna have a little chat.
Shii Ann.
>> I'm gonna pick Rupert,
'cause we're both here alone.
>> PROBST: All right, Rupert,
you and Shii Ann are gonna get a
chance to chat.
Alicia, your pick has been made
for you.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's chat.
>> PROBST: Amber and Jenna,
you're gonna get a little more
time together.
>> Yay!
(laughter)
>> PROBST: So we thought it
might be fun 22 days in to have
a formal chance to get to know
people from the other tribe.
To make it more enjoyable...
we put together a little snack
lunch.
(cheering)
>> Oh, my God! Food.
>> (laughing): Yay! Yay!
>> Thank you!
>> PROBST: Find a spot anywhere
you like, have a private
conversation.
>> I knew this was so
peculiar, I thought it was going
to be something devastating.
>> What a day to pick a
good-looking woman.
>> Oh, shucks, I think
I'm blushing.
>> How perfect is this?
I'm glad we get to relax.
>> I was like, oh, my
God, they have to go find out
about each other.
>> Oh, my God, Rupert!
Let's dig in.
Oh, those are good.
>> So what's it like
over there all by yourself?
Are you getting along?
>> I love Kathy and I
love Lex.
Jerri is nice, but she doesn't
work as hard as the rest of us.
>> I was so happy to get
away from her.
>> I was worried about you
at first.
>> I was worried about me.
You know what?
This game almost broke my
spirit.
>> That's why I'm here.
They cannot get you down.
We got 18 days.
You suck it up, be the stud
you are, put your chest out.
>> It's been a humbling
experience, to say the least.
>> You know, I'm ready for
a merge, I'm ready for all of us
to be one tribe, I'm ready for
individual challenges, I'm
ready to change the game.
>> Rob is really the
dangerous one.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> It seems, because if we go to
individual immunities, that guy
is going to win and win and win
and win and win.
>> I know.
>> And win.
>> The fact that we're
having this picnic leads me to
believe that we are going to
merge.
They're just... waiting.
>> PROBST: Fall in right in
here.
Any order.
All right, drop your buffs.
>> Here we go.
>> PROBST: Drop them at your
feet-- time for some new buffs.
Lex.
Reach in and pick a buff.
You're now a member of Chapera.
Have a spot on the red map.
>> Wow.
This is sweet.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob...
What did you think, we were
merging?
Just switching things up.
Look at that, you're now a
member of Mogo Mogo.
You look good in green.
>> I like red.
>> PROBST: Big Tom.
Another member of Mogo Mogo.
Sticking with Boston Rob.
You'll still be living as two
separate tribes, it's just new
tribes, that's the only
difference.
Jerri, member of Chapera.
So far, nothing has changed but
the color of the buffs.
>> Wow, that's weird.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob, you don't
look pleased about this.
>> They get our camp now?
We're not pleased.
Shii Ann, Chapera.
It continues.
>> Weird.
>> PROBST: Rupert, you going to
be with your old fellas now?
Look at that.
>> Oh, my God!
>> God!
>> PROBST: So far, six tribe
members have picked buffs and
everything is exactly flipped.
Maybe Kathy will find a new
tribe.
Unbelievable.
>> Weird.
This is weird.
>> PROBST: Something about these
tribes is just meant to be.
All right, Alicia.
You got green.
Still no change to the make-up
of each tribe.
>> This is just weird.
>> It is weird.
>> PROBST: We have two buffs
left, one red, one green.
Jenna.
Mogo Mogo.
Amber is the only one to change
tribes.
You stay with Chapera but your
tribe members are all new.
>> Hi, guys.
I'll show you around camp.
>> PROBST: Kind of weird, huh,
Rupert?
>> Very weird.
>> PROBST: Like it was meant to
be.
>> Well, Amber should be here.
>> Amber should be here.
>> The only change is Amber.
All right, so, Lex, Jerri,
Amber, Shii Ann, Kathy, you will
be living now at Chapera's camp.
Boston Rob, Big Tom, Alicia,
Rupert, Jenna, you're going to
Mogo Mogo.
Everything you left at camp this
morning belongs to the new
owners: the Hawaiian sling, the
fish you may have caught, ready
to eat.
Head on out to your new homes.
>> This is crazy.
>> Amber.
>> Thanks for being
our hostess.
>> I definitely feel like
I'm the one who got screwed in
this whole situation.
Kind of nice that I'm still back
at home.
Gosh, I was so mad.
When Jeff held up the new pot
full of buffs and we're all
picking them out, one by one,
really, the main thought that
was going through my head was,
"Let me just pull the same color
that Rob pulls."
This is our camp.
This is our swing.
>> Look at the sofa.
>> Oh, my God, look
at your sofa!
>> This is our lounge chair.
We have a toilet.
>> We came back to our
new home, I realized immediately
that we were so much better off
over here.
I was so excited.
>> This is so cool.
>> It's beautiful.
It's nice to have someplace to
sit besides...
>> And a place for your
feet, too.
>> Oh, my gosh, it is paradise.
>> It's the freakin' Four
Seasons.
>> And there's so much wood
here.
>> They have huge
stacks of logs and dry wood.
There's embers in the fire.
There's a swing and a bench and,
you know, a kitchen area.
I mean, it's an organized,
beautiful camp.
>> So you like it?
>> I'm really-- I'm just amazed.
>> Yeah!
>> We almost cried for joy when
we saw the welcome-to-your-new-
home basket of food and drink.
(cheering)
>> Wow.
Look at the bread.
The cheese is so good, you guys.
>> Toast to... welcome to
your new home.
Hope I can make it as
comfortable as possible.
>> You already have.
You already have, Amber.
To some civilized talk and food.
>> To more fun.
It's a little strange having
everybody here.
It's definitely not home without
the people that belong here.
It kind of sucks.
>> The new Mogo Mogo
definitely got the short end of
this stick, because we inherited
a camp that is in complete
disarray.
>> I have to go get
water, and they only have
one pot, so...
>> They obviously
haven't maintained anything.
Their shelter is tiny.
They have very little firewood.
They haven't cleaned up around
camp.
>> You guys don't want
to try to like make a new
shelter or nothing?
You want to just...
>> I say we try to make
the roof better on that one.
I know how bad you want to build
another shelter.
>> It isn't that.
I just want to be able to sleep
at night and I don't think I'll
be able to sleep in that thing.
>> Now, all of a sudden, we have
to make a living here-- no
blankets, no pillows, nothing.
It's a crap camp.
It's in the middle of nettles.
I don't know why they built it
where they did.
It's practically getting washed
away by the tide, which is
extremely high.
They lost their saws, their
cooking pot, it's a mess.
>> Look at that.
That red...
>> Wow.
>> One nice thing, when
we got here, there was a huge
tray of food, and we immediately
sat down and started eating it.
But, you know, losing Amber and
losing our camp all in one fell
swoop, we didn't feel like we
had too much to celebrate.
>> It's a shame Amber's not
here.
>> It is.
>> It is a shame.
>> They got all our rice.
They got the spear back, they
got the shelter, they got all
the food, they got all the
blankets, they got all the
pillows, they got everything.
>> Well, you know what's
nice about this?
Let them be impressed with what
we've done.
They're going to go there and
realize how well we've been
living.
Maybe that will knock 'em down
even further, 'cause they suck.
>> Oh, God.
>> Conditioner.
>> There's the shampoo.
>> We're going to wash our hair.
My hair is so nappy.
>> I had a feeling that
the shampoo and the toothbrush
were going to be the first
things they grabbed.
So things like that are hard.
>> Chaperans rock!
I love being a Chaperan.
>> They're already
making themselves at home, it's
kind of weird, but something I'm
going to have to get used to.
This is the new home.
It's the new Chapera.
>> I was at my lowest
point this morning.
Those guys are kicking
themselves.
Unfair trade.
>> I hope she's all
right; I really do.
>> Amber?
She'll be okay.
>> She's got to be
hurting though.
>> Yeah, she's got to be.
>> I wish it were me.
I would have been able to handle
it a lot better.
I care about her.
It kills me to have her over
there over by herself.
I know she's tough, but...
...so much of the reason why she
was having such a good time, and
why I was having such a good
time, was because of each other.
Here's to Amber.
>> To Amber.
>> Hope she makes it.
>> Damn straight.
>> Yeah, she'll make it.
>> I don't really care that the
other team has our camp now.
I don't even really care
that they have all of our
possessions.
As much as we're crying about it
over here, it doesn't matter.
What aggravates me is they got
my girl over there.
>> The flag is up.
Our first tree mail as Chapera.
>> What is it?
>> It's a book.
"Mike fell in a fire.
Susan's 'rats and snakes.'
Ghandia screamed, 'You're way
too close.'
The Amazon Women had what it
takes.
Seven countries later,
112 Have played the game.
How well you know your history
determines who will remain."
>> Wow.
>> Wow!
>> Okay. Mike fell in the fire.
Mike caught the pig.
>> Keith couldn't make rice.
Kell got caught with beef jerky.
>> We were boning up on our
Survivor trivia before we went
to the challenge and kind of
trying to forecast what
questions would be asked.
>> Thailand.
John Raymond.
>> One of the things we
went over was the first person
booted from every
single Survivor.
>> Pearl Islands.
>> That girl.
>> With the dress.
>> You don't remember the name
of the woman in the blue dress.
>> No.
>> What else?
>> This is probably the
most important challenge yet to
me, throughout the entire game,
'cause I really feel that by
wining this challenge, I'm
either keeping my life going in
the game of Survivor or ending
my life in the game of Survivor.
>> How many Jennas
have played this game?
>> Two, two Jennas.
>> How many Robs?
>> Four.
>> I promised Amber I
would take her to the end with
me, but I've got to figure out a
way to get her there.
I'm gonna do whatever I can do
to keep her around as long as
possible over there.
Pretty much the next move I make
is gonna have consequences for
everybody left in this game--
serious consequences.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Take back the immunity idol.
You guys didn't earn it, but you
inherited it had and you became
the Chapera Tribe.
Doesn't matter.
Immunity is back up for grabs.
Let's get to today's immunity
challenge.
It's going to test your
knowledge about something you
should know a lot about:
Survivor.
I'm going ask you a series of
questions pertaining to
Survivors one through seven.
There are a equal number of
questions from each.
I'll draw them randomly from
this bin.
It's a tribal challenge.
You will confer, give me one
answer.
The first tribe to ten wins
immunity, guaranteed a one-in-
nine shot of being the sole
survivor in this all-star
edition, and a one-in-nine shot
at a million bucks.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Take a spot on the
bench.
>> PROBST: Ready to get started?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: First question.
"In the Marquesas, which
survivor's arrival at camp was
best described by another tribe
member as 'almost like
Cleopatra'?"
Confer, write it down and don't
reveal till I ask you to.
Let's reveal.
"Sarah, Sarah."
Both tribes say Sarah.
Both tribes are right: 1-1.
Next question: "In Africa, which
unlikely pair shared a date at
the drive-in movie?"
Let's reveal.
Mogo Mogo says "Frank and
Brandon."
Chapera says "Brandon and
Frank."
You're both right.
Another point for both tribes.
We're tied up 2-2.
"In what country did Survivor:
Africa take place?"
>> What is it?
>> PROBST: Reveal.
Chapera says "Kenya."
That's right.
Mogo Mogo says "Nairobi."
That's wrong.
Chapera scores.
3-2 lead.
>> Nice, nice.
>> PROBST: "In Survivor: Borneo
what specifically did the
"survivors eat in the first-ever
food-eating challenge?"
>> Is that right?
>> Yes.
>> Good... I mean, the
right term?
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Reveal.
Jenna specifically says: "Butok
(bug larvae.)"
Butok is right.
Chapera says "grubs."
"Grubs" is not specific enough,
not right.
We're tied up 3-3.
>> I was wondering if it
was too broad.
>> PROBST: Again from Survivor
I: "Which of the original
castaways used the alphabet
strategy when voting tribe
members off the island?"
>> No. Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Both tribes reveal.
Chapera says "Dr. Sean."
Mogo Mogo says "Dr. Sean."
Both right.
We're tied up at four.
"Which outback survivor had to
be airlifted out of the game?"
Reveal.
"Mike Skupin, Mike Skupin."
Both tribes right.
We are still tied 5-5.
Next question: "Which Marquesas
survivor picked the unlucky
purple stone during a Tribal
Council tiebreaker resulting
in their exit from the game?"
Reveal.
"Paschal. Paschal."
You're both right.
You're tied at 6-6.
"In Survivor: Thailand, whom did
Rob Zubotnik grab by the neck
and toss in the water during a
challenge?"
Reveal.
Chapera says "Clay."
Mogo Mogo says "Clay."
Clay is right.
You're still tied, 7-7.
"In the Pearl Islands, who was a
mortician?"
Both tribes reveal.
Chapera says "Darrah."
Mogo Mogo says "Darrah."
"Darrah" is correct.
>> I remember Darrah.
(wolf whistles)
>> PROBST: We remain tied, 8-8.
"In the Pearl Islands, which
castaway had to be rescued by
tribe mates during a water
challenge?"
Reveal.
Both tribes say "Osten."
Both tribes are right.
We are 9-9.
"What was Kell accused of
smuggling into the outback by
his tribe?"
Reveal.
"Beef jerky" is right.
We're tied up at ten.
We move into a tie-breaker.
It's going to be a time trial.
You'll have 30 seconds to answer
this question.
"Name the first person voted off
each Survivor in order."
Begin.
(whispering)
>> PROBST: Ten seconds.
Rob working it for Mogo Mogo.
(whispering)
Got some last-minute additions.
>> We're done.
>> PROBST: The tribe with the
most correct will win immunity.
Reveal.
Chapera, you say: "Sonya, Deb,
Diane, Peter, John and Ryan."
Those first six are right.
Number seven, you said "Kim."
That is wrong.
>> Aw...
>> PROBST: You got six of seven.
Mogo Mogo you say: "Sonya, Deb,
Diane, Peter, John, Brian and
Nicole."
Mogo Mogo is right.
You win immunity.
Congratulations.
Who wants it?
>> I'll grab it for us.
>> PROBST: You're going to be
the grabber of immunity?
>> I'm the taker.
>> PROBST: It seems to stick
with you guys, no matter what
color buff you're wearing.
Chapera, sadly, Tribal Council
tonight.
Somebody else from your tribe
going home.
I'll see you there.
Head on back.
>> If you can, if you can.
>> PROBST: Lex, move it out.
>> Kind of a bittersweet win
there.
>> Very bittersweet.
We did what we needed to do,
but...
>> You're exactly right.
>> ...at the expense of
one of our own.
>> Today, after the challenge
was over, I grabbed Lex.
I said, "If you can save Amber,
I'll remember it, and I'll help
you later on in the game."
If Lex is smart, he'll keep her
around.
>> To hoping that Amber can
figure out some damn way
to stay.
>> I hope you make it.
>> Hope you make it, Amber.
>> Today is hard.
It's wicked hard.
It hurts a lot.
More than anything in the world,
I want to take Amber to the
final two.
I put an "A" on my arm for
Amber.
Hopefully she makes it to the
next challenge.
>> Keeps on rolling, man,
at Chapera. God!
We got back from the challenge,
and we lost once again.
What else is new?
>> That's a drag.
>> So, the interesting
dynamic that occurred was, at
the end of the challenge, Boston
Rob went up to Lex and said, "To
protect Amber, I'll protect
you."
I overheard it, and it's such a
godfather move.
>> What do you want to do?
'Cause we've got to make our
decision fast.
>> Well, the thing is, if
we keep Amber, we are totally
sucking up to Mariano.
>> We are, and I don't
think Mariano's going to last
that long.
Kathy and I are trying to figure
out where the possibilities are.
And so far, it still looks like
we're going to have to vote out
Amber.
>> You know, Amber is never
going to be on our side ever.
>> No. That would be the
simplest thing.
You vote off Amber, that's one
less original Chaperan.
However...
>> Mariano is just going
to flip.
>> Mariano's going to flip.
He has never, ever...
>> He's got to be pissed,
though, that he's losing his
chick.
>> If we take Amber out,
Rob Mariano's going to be
pretty upset.
And he's going to... the wrath
of God will come down upon us.
> So, Amber-Gamber...
>> So, Kathy?
I'm voting for Jerri.
That's my desperate attempt.
Well, we lost the immunity
challenge, so now it's strategy.
What am I going to do?
I think I'm a better player than
Jerri.
>> You are.
>> And I'm stronger in
the challenges than Jerri.
>> So, how are you going to get
us convinced to vote for Jerri?
(both chuckling)
>> Do you want me to get
down on my knees and beg?
Please, Kathy, keep me in the
game.
Vote for Jerri.
Right now, I'm just going to try
to make a lot of deals and
promise them a longer time in
the game if they promise me a
longer time in the game.
This is the deal.
In the end, it comes down to
you, Lex, me, Rob and Big Tom.
That's what I think.
>> How do we convince Lex
to get rid of Jerri?
>> Well, doesn't he think
that Big Tom will be on our side
in the end?
>> He does think Big Tom
will be on our side, yeah.
And he thinks Rob will come
over, too.
>> So...
>> Um, but he's stuck on
this tribal loyalty thing.
I'll talk to Lex about it.
I've just been talking to Amber,
and, um, I actually think it
might make sense to keep her.
Just because, if we do merge,
Mariano is going to carry a
grudge on that one.
>> (sighing): All right.
>> I know.
>> I need a little time
to think about this.
>> I know.
'Cause I think Mariano is going
to hold a grudge.
You do realize that he's going
to kind of be pissed.
>> If we delivered, I think
he would deliver.
>> He will deliver.
>> The only thing about this
that just reeks is that it
is just... it is absolutely
horrible for Jerri.
>> I know it is.
>> But I do think that I
can exploit the favor...
>> Please!
>> ...to our advantage.
>> Yeah.
>> Instead of getting rid
of Amber tonight, the decision
to vote Jerri out instead makes
more strategic sense.
So... I need to tell Jerri.
You know I love you.
>> Oh, no.
>> And you know I have to
be straight with you.
>> Oh, no.
Explain to me why.
>> Well, with the way
things are going with the other
tribe... and the alliances that
have been made over there, it's
a stronger, more secure play.
>> I don't understand,
like, how everything
switched so drastically.
I mean, is it because Amber gave
up some information or...?
>> There's some information
that was passed to me by Rob...
at the challenge.
>> Boston Rob will tell you
anything to keep Amber around.
It's so obvious.
He will say anything.
He's got the hots for her, and
they've got some sort of thing
going on.
He will stab you in the back the
second he gets the chance.
Please reconsider, Lex.
You're giving up somebody who
has your back to the very end,
and... that right there is
priceless.
>> Let me... let me think
some more.
I mean, I... I don't believe in
ever making a decision without
thinking about stuff, so...
This is when the game really...
takes a turn and changes... when
you have to start making really
hard decisions.
>> What happened?
>> We're trying to hash
this out.
>> Yeah, Jerri's just
pleading her case.
So, we just want to make sure
before we blip somebody off into
the stratosphere.
>> That we're thinking
about everything.
>> Yeah.
>> All the options
for all of us.
>> All the options when
we get over there.
>> We probably shouldn't have
told her.
>> Oh, no, you had to.
>> No, no, no...
>> No, I mean, I'm glad
we did, but now...
>> 'Cause it's making us
think of things we hadn't
thought about.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> So, we're going to
Tribal Council, and no matter
what decision we make, nights
like tonight are just, uh...
miserable.
>> PROBST: Hello, guys.
Let's talk about the past few
days.
We brought both tribes together,
the idea being, we would shuffle
the tribes.
The former Mogo Mogo stayed
completely together.
The only thing that changed is
you gained a member.
Two big events really transpired
when this went down.
First one was, you got a new
home.
Kathy?
>> Oh! (scoffs)
I mean, you know, it's a
four-star hotel, you know?
We're coming from the 3-M Motel
over on Mogo Mogo, so it's so
much better.
And you know, I mean, I was
embarrassed that we didn't go a
little further with our camp for
those poor guys.
But no, it's great!
I mean, we couldn't be happier.
And can you see you get
stronger.
>> PROBST: The other big result
of this tribe shuffle was one
person shuffled, and that was
you, Amber.
And the look on your face...
>> Yeah, I was extremely upset.
It was... it was impossible to
hide.
And that first night, it was
really hard.
But I woke up the next morning
and told myself, "It's a new
day, and so, I'm not going to
let myself get down."
I had one down night, and that
next morning I woke up, and I
was a new tribe.
>> PROBST: So, just like that,
the loyalty you had with Boston
Rob and Big Tom and everybody
else on your old tribe is gone?
>> I can't make any guesses
what's going to happen in this
game, so I have to play with my
new members, and these are my
new tribe members.
>> PROBST: Shii Ann, it's got to
be a little hard to trust that.
Obviously, odd person out.
So, when she says, "Hey, I'm
with you guys," what's the part
of you going, "Hmm, I don't
know?"
>> I mean, it would be
silly to think her, you know, 20
some-odd days with those guys is
just erased by the last three
days.
But she's a member of Chapera,
just like the rest of us, and
trust is something that is built
one day at a time here.
>> PROBST: Jerri, this was a
reunion for you.
>> Yeah. I was just like,
"Oh, my Outback sister, she's
back with me!" you know?
It was... it was very exciting,
but I also realized that it's a
totally different game.
Everyone has come into this game
with different personalities and
with different goals.
>> PROBST: Lex, in a way, was it
nice to get Amber?
Because really, your tribe could
stay intact, and you could get
rid of the opposition, after
having come to a Tribal Council.
>> I'd be lying if I said
it was any other way.
And I think that, you know,
that's just a harsh reality of
the game.
But we all know the game has so
many twists and turns, it ain't
over until it's over.
>> PROBST: Amber, if it's you
tonight...
>> If it's me tonight, I
know that I went out trying as
hard as I possibly could not to
go.
So, if I'm leaving tonight, I'm
leaving tonight fighting hard to
stay in.
>> PROBST: It is time to vote.
Lex, you're up.
>> Amber, I'm very proud of the
way you're playing this game.
You did go down fighting.
>> It's crazy that it's
come down to me voting you out
to keep myself in this game.
I owe you a huge thanks for
that.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Jerri.
Amber.
One vote Amber, one vote Jerri.
Jerri.
That's two votes Jerri, one vote
Amber.
Ninth person voted out of
Survivor: All-Stars...
Jerri.
That's three votes.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> I just want you guys
to know, it's been an honor
playing this game with you.
Thank you.
(chuckling): I'm going to go
eat some chocolate.
>> PROBST: Jerri, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, tonight's Tribal Council
proved something once again.
It ain't over till it's over.
Grab your torches.
Go back to camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
The game is on.
>> I made promises that I
don't know if I'm going to be
able to keep, but at least I got
myself three more days.
>> PROBST: Not knowing Amber's
fate, Rob makes a new plan...
>> I made an alliance with
Alicia, and now I've got
one with everyone.
>> PROBST: ...and goes back on
his word.
>> I'm sorry you feel that way.
I really, truly am.
>> This has truly been,
again, a life-changing
experience.
I think I've done the
impossible.
I have found a way to find peace
in a very stressful situation,
and now I'm ready to go out into
the world and see what other
craziness I can conquer.