>> JEFF PROBST: I'm standing on
the rim of Mt. Yasur, a massive
crater that displays its anger
on a regular basis, spewing
molten lava and rock thousands
of feet into the air.
Locals believe this is the final
resting spot for the spirits
of the dead.
Yasur is one of nine active
volcanoes on the island nation
of Vanuatu in the South Pacific.
It is a land with a fascinating
history of cannibalism, where
rituals like sorcery and black
magic are still a part of
daily life.
It is here that 18 Americans are
about to begin the adventure of
a lifetime.
18 strangers, all from different
walks of life, forced to work
together to create a new society
while battling the elements and
each other.
They must learn to adapt, or
they'll be voted out of the
tribe.
In the end, only one will remain
to claim the million-dollar
prize.
39 days, 18 people, one
Survivor.
♪ ♪
( yelling )
>> There he is.
>> Thank God.
( whistling )
>> PROBST: Yeah.
( applause and cheering )
Welcome to Survivor: Vanuatu--
Islands of Fire.
The game is about to begin, but
before it does, you have to be
granted access to the land.
So you're going to take part in
a tribal ritual.
It is a rite of passage and an
invitation to stay on the land,
but in order to stay, you must
participate.
It's going to impact each of you
differently.
At times, you may find it
beautiful.
At times, you may be repulsed.
And at times, you may be
frightened.
Chief Mormor will preside over
all of this.
He is a real chief.
I will be there, but he will
guide you through it.
The tribes of Vanuatu take their
spirituality very seriously.
The ceremony you're going to
take part in is an authentic
Vanuatu tribal tradition.
You are in a foreign country.
Remember that.
This is their culture.
We are only visitors.
It's time to go over.
Three in a canoe.
Down the rope ladder.
>> Jeff gave us an overview,
saying how the customs
of Vanuatu are not like we're
used to, so I was... I was
really nervous after he was
talking to us.
I'm like, "What are they going
to do?"
>> Jeff informed us we're going
to climb down the side of the
boat and we're going to get in
these canoes.
I thought, 'Man, that's great,'
because I didn't learn how to
swim until six weeks before I
come here.
I would've been spooked if I
knew I had to swim.
( screaming )
>> We get into the boat, and it
tips over, so I'm trying to hold
onto the rope to keep me up.
It was killing my back, but I
wasn't about to move again.
I was going to stay right where
I was at.
We finally got another boat
over there.
( singing )
( chanting )
>> When the natives took
us into the middle of the ring
where everybody circled around
us, it was really overwhelming
for me, and I don't know if it
was just the anticipation of
getting started or the whole
thing, but I was... really, I
was moved to tears.
( native people screaming )
>> There was a bunch of
tribesmen running with spears.
My first reaction was, you know,
"What's going on?"
We were like, "Wha-Wha-What?
Are we suppose to defend
ourselves?
What are we supposed to do?"
>> They're jabbing spears at
absolutely everybody except me.
Nobody jabbed a spear at me in
any way, shape or form, which I
took as, you know, a black man
coming on the island is not
particularly unwelcome.
( singing )
>> These guys in their big
cone-shaped jungle dresses--
they have these big sticks, and
they start, you know, pulling
people out with the sticks, but
kind of, like, you know,
whacking 'em out.
Soon enough, I noticed that they
were bringing the women to one
side.
We look over, and the guys, you
know...
Like, we're, like, kneeling on a
mat, and they all have, like,
little, like, stump seats
to sit on.
And they're, like, right in the
center of the action.
We're kind of off to the side.
And so I immediately start
thinking, 'What's with this?
I thought we were all supposed
to be part of this ceremony.'
>> They brought a bowl out,
and they uncovered the palm
leaves off of it, and they were
pointing at it.
Well, I thought maybe I was
supposed to wash my fingers or
something, you know?
Uh, we were getting ready to eat
something or-or, uh, wash my
fingers, 'cause it was some
rustic-looking stuff.
>> Chief Mormor offers each one
of us this kava, which is the
local drink.
It's like mud, basically.
You drink it.
Your lips go numb, and your
tongue goes numb, and your
throat goes numb.
( spitting )
( laughing )
>> The chief is welcoming us,
and I look over at the girls,
and they're not getting anything
to drink.
And I'm thinking, 'Wow, this is
pretty cool.'
You know, special treatment for
the guys.
( spitting )
>> I was waiting for our turn.
I was like, "Well, okay, well,
when do we get kava?"
But it never came around.
We're not getting the full
deal here.
I'm not used to being put second
behind a man.
( man chanting )
( men singing in response )
>> PROBST: Keep if mind, guys,
what is about to happen next is
a common part of their tribal
tradition.
>> Apparently, the Vanuatu
people really honor pigs.
Pigs are, I think, sometimes
better than women.
Anyway, so, they come in with
this pig.
Right away, I thought, 'Okay,
we're having a pig roast,' you
know?
But I thought the pig was dead.
And then I realized the pig
was alive.
>> I eat meat, and I know that
animals are slaughtered, but,
like, seeing it was just like...
( gasps )
Like, I-I literally think I
gasped out loud, because it was
just so shocking to watch.
>> That kind of stuff doesn't
bother me, because I'm a
shepherdess, and that's
what I do.
I-I raise lambs for that exact
purpose: to slaughter.
So I totally understand
that ritual.
>> The head chief took the
blood of his sacrifice and went
to each male member of
Survivor-- no, no females--
and said, "You are now a-a, you
know, a warrior in Vanuatu."
And basically, I felt what he
was doing was he was saying
"Welcome."
( cheering )
>> PROBST: There's one element
left to this initiation.
It involves a spiritual stone.
It is believed on these lands
that this carved stone and other
stones like it ward off evil
spirits.
Last thing you want in this game
is bad luck.
Possessing this stone could give
you a spiritual advantage
in the game.
As you've seen, men and women
are treated very differently.
The chief is offering the men a
chance to possess this stone.
The only hitch is you have to
get it from the top of that
pole, which has been greased
with pig fat.
If you fail, the women get it.
The chief will decide in which
order you go.
To show you that it can be done,
he's going to instruct a tribe
member to take it up and put it
there now.
>> Ever who possesses
that stone, the spirits are
supposed to be in favor.
Even though that's not my
beliefs, I still wanted that
stone, just so the girls
wouldn't get it.
( cheering and hooting )
>> We were all going, "I
don't want to be the one that
falls flat on my face in front
of everybody."
The chief turned around, and he
pointed in my direction.
I was like, "Oh, my God.
No, not me."
And I went like this out of the
way.
I said, "Yeah, him?"
( cheering )
>> I was just praying to
God he was going to pick
somebody else, but he picked me.
As soon as he did, I figured the
only way I'd even have any
chance is to do it kind of like
the other guy did it.
And I got a little dirt on my
feet, in my hands.
And I just hung on for dear
life.
>> The girls were praying
that the boys were not
going to do it.
So I was like, "Please fall."
We want to see some of them fall
at least.
( cheering )
( thunder crashing )
>> As soon as he got that
rock, it started raining
like pouring pee out of
a boot on a flat rock.
It was definitely spooky, but I
didn't care, we got the rock.
( cheering )
>> Now, it's time to begin
Survivor.
Because you have been divided by
the chief into groups of men and
women, you will stay that way.
Men in possession of the
Spiritual Stone, you are the
Lopevi Tribe.
You will wear red.
>> Men against women.
It's perfect.
I can outsmart eight men a hell
of a lot quicker than I can
outsmart eight women.
Women stick together.
They're thick as thieves.
Men are deceiving, mischievous,
untrusting human beings.
Men-- I can manipulate.
>> PROBST: You are the Yasur
Tribe.
Named after the volcano.
You will wear yellow.
>> When I found out we was
splitting the men and the
women, I looked around at them
little girls and I thought, "Oh,
Lord, what did you get me into?"
We had a couple of ol' prissy
ones.
They probably hadn't even been
dirty in their entire days and
they ain't got a clue what's in
store for the next God knows how
many days.
>> PROBST: Your next task is to
find your tribal beaches.
You will not have a map to guide
you.
You will not have fire to lead
the way.
It is going to be a long, dark,
wet walk.
And when you get there, you will
have a pot, you will have a
machete and you will have a map
to water, and that's it.
Have a good 39 days.
Men, down the beach this way.
Keep walking till you find your
tribe flag.
( thunder crashing )
Ladies, down to the beach, head
right.
( cheering )
>> I think the boys got a lot
more out of that ceremony than
we did.
I think we definitely got a bum
deal.
So we're out for blood now.
( cheering )
>> Okay, girls. Be really
careful. >> You have to hold on
to the next person.
>> This is really slippery roots
here so be really careful.
>> Oh, whoa, Scout.
>> One down, one up.
>> Are you okay?
>> Yeah.
>> What do you think, Scout?
I'm going with your years of
experience and... and, uh, know-
how here, because I don't want
to... I don't want to walk
around all night.
>> I just wanted to hunker down
till daylight came so we could,
you know, find our camp easier
and everybody would be safe.
I wasn't tired.
I just love to sit and visit.
I haven't said anything to
anybody here, but I'm schlepping
around an artificial knee.
So I'm pretty cautious crawling
across lava rock that deep at
night with it raining.
( hooting )
>> Yeah?
>> Ami and Dolly and Scout
didn't want to come along.
They almost insisted on just
stopping where we were and, you
know, sleeping.
Like, I think sleeping right
here is, like, the stupidest
thing we could possibly do.
>> You guys, come on up here!
>> Come on.
>> We want to hang out.
We want to get to know each
other.
>> We want you to come
hang out with us.
>> Hey, girls, let's make
a group decision.
What way do you want to go?
>> I don't want to hold you.
I want you guys to go at your
pace, you know.
I just, I feel like they're
headed the wrong direction, so
I want you to go on.
I'm happy to stay back.
>> Somebody needs to make
a decision.
>> It got to a point
where we couldn't make a
decision whether we should
continue or go back or if we
missed the flag, or...
We were really kind of afraid
that we missed camp altogether
'cause it's dark out.
>> I really had my heart set
on find our camp tonight.
>> Me, too.
>> I didn't want to be too pushy
because I didn't want to be,
like, the odd person out.
>> Are you going to be able to
sleep in this rain and cold?
>> No, no, I want to keep
walking.
>> We might as well keep
>> Luckily, you know,
other people agreed with me
that, um, we should continue.
Scout, will you come with us
if we chose to go, or are you
going to...?
>> Yeah, I'll go with you.
>> Come on, girl.
>> Yeah, let's go forward.
>> We don't want the guys
to find their camp before us.
( scattered laughing )
>> I know, I know.
>> Whoo!
>> It's the blind leading
the blind here.
>> Where's the flag, bro?
>> I don't think nine of
us would miss it.
>> Can we hold on a quick
second?
We really need to come up with
some sort of game plan because
this walking our path is bull...
I mean, we got nine of us.
There's got to be a better way
than this.
Now we can keep walking along
the path, and some of us can
walk along the path, but then
we passed several trails that
are going up, and we have no
idea where those things are
going.
Nine of us walking in a group
like a bunch of ladies ain't
helping.
>> Rory, I don't think
he's going to fit in.
There is one in every bunch, you
know what I mean?
To see, like, Rory already
barking out orders, what is he
thinking?
I'll be honest with you, the
walk is, like, kind of keeping
us busy, like, we got something
to do, just walk.
Like, you know what I mean?
Once we find camp anyway, what
are we going to do when we get
there anyway?
>> What does the group want
to do?
What do we want to do?
>> Keep walking?
>> Move on.
>> Move out, move out.
>> I don't think there was
any independent thought.
I think that we could've covered
more ground if we weren't all
walking in a big pack of nine
guys all at once.
Some of the younger guys that...
that are here, none of them want
to listen.
They're all young.
>> Little tension on
the first night.
( scattered chuckling )
>> What's that right there?
Does that look like a stick with
a flag on it?
Yo, it's the flag!
( whooping )
We got the flag!
>> Yeah!
( talking excitedly )
>> Let's be real careful.
>> This has got to be it.
>> Please be our beach,
please be our beach, please be
our beach.
>> Yeah!
( whooping and cheering )
You guys, we did it!
( cheering )
We see the flag and, you know,
all the trouble, all the
conflicts, like, dissolved.
We're all hugging and thrilled
to death that we're here.
>> Here's to be persevering
and being strong!
( cheering loudly )
( whooping )
>> Okay, now what?
( scattered laughing )
>> Should we bring the rest
of the fronds over?
>> I think now let's pull in
what we got and see and then
tie 'em down.
You got to tie all these up to
that center piece.
Boy, we've got a really sturdy
rack for a shelter.
It's been a group effort.
I've stayed with it, and Twila
has stayed with it, and, uh,
Leann stayed with it.
But some of the gals are down
there on the beach basking in
the sun, chitchatting.
>> Oh, praise the spirit
for the sun.
>> Rub it on.
>> It's scrub, deodorant.
Shampoo.
>> I call all these
sorority girls "bowheads."
That's what we call them back in
Oklahoma.
They all like to hang together.
They're like cattle.
I mean, really, cows, they just
cluster.
And those sorority chicks, they
aren't paying attention to any
damn thing but themselves.
You know, they're their favorite
topic.
>> I'm really not a
negative person.
Like, I'm awfully optimistic
in most cases, but for some
reason, I just don't think we're
going to get fire from rubbing
two, like, quasi dry sticks
together.
>> Eliza, she talks nonstop.
She's probably at the top of my
list, just to get her mouth out
of my face.
I'm telling you.
>> Dude, are they building
shelter right now?
I don't see them.
>> Just lean up against
this and hold that.
Slide down a little bit, though.
( chuckles )
>> Twila has been working
on the shelter constantly.
I feel like her continuous work
has made those of us who have
taken reasonable breaks look bad
in her mind to think that, oh,
they're not pulling their
weight.
Hey, ladies, looking great.
>> We had too much chattering
and not enough moving.
Mouths are working but the hands
ain't.
The hut still is not done.
There is a couple of them that
didn't do nothing but bitch,
moan and complain last night.
We was all cold.
You know, get off your ass, get
the... done or don't bitch about
it tonight when you're freezing
your butt off.
>> We know where our
water source is.
It's just a little creek with
some fresh water.
It looks really clean, but it's
still going to have to be
boiled, and... I guess our
problem right now is we just got
to get a fire going.
>> Hey, you guys, before we
start the fire, let's
get the, uh, let's get the
Immunity Rock, huh?
Rub the rock's head.
>> Fire.
>> Well, you know, it worked
at home when I did this.
You make a little notch in this
fire tray and put the ball of
tinder right in here.
On the opposite side, you make a
groove.
The Aborigines did this, why
can't we?
>> J.P. wants to prove himself
bad.
He's about 30 years old, and
he's feeling like, you know, I'm
buff, I'm bad, I'm young, I'm
all, you know, go to the end of
this.
He don't have a clue.
He's got the frame, but he ain't
got the brain.
>> Slackening.
>> Yup, there you go, dude.
Keep it going.
>> Yup.
>> This is going to be it.
Keep going.
>> Ton of smoke, ton of smoke.
>> We need more smoke,
more smoke, dude.
( grunting )
>> Dump it...
Blow it...
>> It's here...
It's right here, it's right
here, it's right here.
>> We actually had a hot
ember, which was very pink.
>> Oh, you're getting it.
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> Just go, go, go.
>> Easy, easy...
>> I think we were all excited
to see a hot ember, but none of
us knew what to do with it.
We were just kind of like,
"Yeah, we've got ember."
No.
>> No!
>> We were so close to
getting fire going that I
thought we were gonna be
able to boil water.
Didn't work.
>> You got those leaves?
>> You guys check it out.
I got to...
I got to show you this.
>> There's one more right now.
>> You guys agree that I
had a pretty good run down here,
I didn't fall or anything?
>> After doing things that
are physically demanding, I felt
like it was the right time to-to
reveal the fact that I have no
foot, that it's a prosthesis.
They were pretty surprised.
It's a rare form of cancer
called synovial sarcoma.
And I just had a little, uh,
bump in the bottom of my foot...
>> Dude.
>> ...and thought it was
nothing.
I thought it was a cyst.
I lost it about 20 months ago.
>> Dude, it's inspirational
that you're here.
It's awesome.
>> Yeah.
>> I know.
>> Good on you, mate.
>> I had absolutely no
idea that Chad had no leg.
I mean, he had...
He was wearing pants the whole
day, so he just goes, "Hey,
guys, look."
And then he unzippered his
pants, and there was no leg.
It was pretty...
It was pretty shocking.
>> It's, uh...
>> Extremely mobile, man.
You did a hell of a job with it.
>> Well, I try.
>> Great.
The guy with the mechanical
leg's gonna win for sure.
He's nice, he's smart, he's
quiet, and he... you know, he's
got the underdog thing going on,
so we're screwed.
>> That's awesome, dude.
I had no idea.
>> I'm amazed.
All the power to him.
I totally think that's
inspirational, but if I have
to vote his ass out of here
tomorrow, I'm still gonna vote
his ass out of here tomorrow.
>> Let's go.
>> Tree mail.
>> Whoo!
>> How cool.
>> I know.
>> Is this it?
>> "A show of pride and unity,
each time the two tribes meet.
Bring your tribal flag with you
whenever you complete."
>> Compete.
"Access..."
>> "Assess your tribe mates
strengths.
Whose talents you'll require."
>> Mm-hmm.
>> "One tribe leaves with heads
hung low, the others go home
with fire."
( gasping and cheering )
>> They don't have it.
They don't have it.
>> We got tree mail, and,
um, we're all psyched up, 'cause
supposedly we're gonna get some
fire.
>> Obviously, most people
think that girls are weaker, and
women aren't cut out for this
kind of thing, so I think it's
really important that we win
this challenge.
We're gonna go and kick some
butt.
>> PROBST: Yasur, the ladies,
how is it going so far?
Two nights.
>> Two long, cold...
>> No fire.
>> ...wet nights.
>> But it's going awesome.
>> PROBST: All right, Lopevi,
you guys, grinning.
No problem, right?
First three days, how is it
going so far?
>> We still need fire before
we're gonna drink water.
So we need to boil ours.
We're not taking any chances.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Let's get to the first
challenge.
It is for both reward and
immunity.
There are several elements.
All nine of you must go under
the mud crawl.
Once all nine of you have made
it to the other size of the mud
crawl, three tribe members will
tackle the box maze.
Your goal is to maneuver a ball
from the start to the finish
net.
Once the ball gets in the net,
take it with you, because it has
matches inside that you're gonna
need later.
The next stage, all nine must
cross a very narrow balance
beam.
If you fall off, or if your feet
hit the net at any time, you got
to go back to the start.
Once all nine have finished,
three different tribe members
will race to build a fire that
will burn a rope and drop a
torch.
Light it, cross the finish line.
First tribe with a lit torch to
cross the finish line and light
the final wok wins reward and
immunity.
Want to know what the reward is?
>> Absolutely.
>> It's flint.
( applause )
>> Yeah!
>> You already have steel
with the machete.
This will give you fire, give
you warmth, let you boil water.
But more important than reward
is this.
Immunity.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: This is what you want
in this game.
If you have immunity, you are
safe.
You cannot be voted out.
Without it, you are vulnerable.
Ready to go?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Take your spots on
the start and wait for my go.
All right.
Here we go for reward and
immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Through the mud pit.
Everybody dead even.
>> Come on.
>> Come on...
Come on.
>> PROBST: Pretty even.
Keep moving.
Get your face down and dig
through.
John and Lisa are across.
>> Come on, go.
Come on...
>> PROBST: A lot of teamwork
going on.
The women pulling each other
through.
Guys pulling each other through.
( people shouting )
Dead even.
Let's go.
Get her through.
Pull him!
Got to get on the mat.
Men are through the mud.
Men moving on to the box maze.
Get on the mat.
Drag her.
Women through the mud.
Women moving on to the box maze.
>> Careful.
Does it need to go over there?
>> It goes here, it
goes here...
>> PROBST: You need the maneuver
the ball into the finish net.
>> Don't let it go in yet.
>> Ready?
Now. Now.
>> We're in.
>> No. Just take your time.
Easy. Right there.
>> PROBST: Guys hit a roadblock.
>> That needs to go through
this one.
>> No, down.
>> Down...
>> Here.
>> Nice.
( indistinct chatter )
>> It won't fit.
>> PROBST: Girls working
together well.
>> Oh, oh.
>> Oh, come on.
>> PROBST: The men have it.
Moving on with their ball to the
balance beam.
>> Nice.
Now, tilt, tilt.
Don't let it go down now.
>> PROBST: Chad first up on the
balance beam.
Keep working.
You're still in this.
>> Now, we can't let it go
through that last one.
>> Okay, okay, bring it back.
I'll bring it back.
>> Don't tilt it.
Just go nice and tiny.
>> PROBST: Bubba is down.
Back to the start.
>> Go, go, go, go...
>> PROBST: John makes it across.
The women have it.
Ladies, you're still in it.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Come on.
>> Go, go, go, go, go...
>> PROBST: Brady, you're across
and down.
>> Go.
>> Come on, women.
Agility, agility.
>> PROBST: Bubba gonna crawl.
Oh, scraping his belly against
that wood.
That cannot feel good.
>> You got it, man.
Come on.
>> Think fire, think fire.
>> Come on, think about it.
>> PROBST: Bubba working it.
>> Let's go, let's go.
She's catching you, she's
passing you.
>> PROBST: You cannot touch any
part of the net.
>> She's passing you.
>> PROBST: Leann makes it.
Women have their first woman
across.
Get those feet up there.
>> Good man.
>> PROBST: Bubba's through.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's go, come on...
>> Go.
>> PROBST: Chad you're there.
Keep moving Twila.
Watch your feet.
Keep 'em up.
That a way.
Drag those feet up.
You're good.
>> Hurry, hurry!
>> PROBST: Lea makes it.
You're down.
Dolly, you're good.
That a way to dig, Rory.
( people shouting )
Mia makes it across.
Women are closing the gap.
That a the way, Rory.
Down to you two.
Down to Scout and Chris.
( all shouting )
>> PROBST: No, Chris to
the back.
Hustle, man, you got it.
Stay in this!
( all shouting )
>> PROBST: Women have taken the
lead.
Hustle, Scout.
You got to get to the mat.
( all shouting )
>> Keep going, keep going.
>> PROBST: Let's go, men.
You're still in it.
Women have to make fire.
>> Start it small.
Start it small then roll around
it.
>> Then we'll grab it.
>> Move forward.
Move forward, buddy.
>> Don't do it...
>> Just like you're walking
on the sidewalk, bro.
>> It's all you, man.
>> He's off again.
He's off again.
>> It's all you, man.
>> Plenty of time, dude.
Take your time.
Focus.
>> Get a few tall sticks
on there.
>> Come on, man, it's all you.
>> Keep your feet straight.
>> Jimmy.
>> Come on, girls.
( indistinct chatter )
>> PROBST: Ladies have fire.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Protect that fire.
Block the wind.
>> You can do this, Chris!
You can do it, man.
Say to yourself, you can do it,
buddy.
>> Just think how warm we'll be
tonight, please.
>> Okay, let's go now.
>> They got as far as... now.
>> Whoo!
>> Look up.
Let's go.
>> It's all you.
It's all you, man.
You're the man.
You got our support.
>> Here we go, here we go.
Here we go.
Keep it going.
>> Go faster, go faster, go
faster, go faster...
>> Go, go, go, go...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Here it goes.
( all shouting )
>> Fire!
>> Oh, fire!
>> There it is.
There it goes!
( indistinct chatter )
>> Go!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Yasur across the
finish line.
The women win the first
challenge-- reward and immunity!
( cheering )
>> WOMEN ( chanting ): Fire and
water and immunity, fire and
water and immunity...!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Yasur, right here.
That's going back to camp.
No Tribal Council for you guys.
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: And flint.
Water tonight.
You'll stay warm.
Congratulations.
>> ALL: Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> In the mood for a hot meal?
>> PROBST: Lopevi, tough break.
Chris, certainly gave it
everything you had.
We'll see if it mattered or not
tonight at Tribal Council.
Somebody is going home.
First person voted out.
I'll see you there.
>> Whoo!
( cheering )
>> Hey, bottom line, I think we
underestimated them, man.
They did a good job.
>> Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we just lost.
>> Losing fire right now
was tough.
Losing to women was tough.
>> I want to tell you guys a
little bit more about myself.
I'm not real good at balance.
( laughter )
>> Chris couldn't get
across the balance beam.
The fact is, he didn't make it,
and we lost.
>> I'd get halfway and hit
a wall.
I really wanted to make it
across the beam.
You know, if I had wings, I'd
have made it.
You know, I would have made
myself go across the beam.
This game, you outwit,
outplay, outlast people.
You don't out-balance them.
>> It has to be.
You know what I'm saying?
>> I totally agree.
>> We have to win this game.
>> Lea, what do you think... who
are you leaning towards tonight?
We're just talking, as a group,
we want to be a strong group.
>> Bottom line is, I
want to beat those girls, and I
want to keep getting immunity.
The way I'm going to do it is,
it's basically the weakest link.
>> I'm going to give it a
few hours and see what the
attitudes are, 'cause, I mean, I
like everybody.
>> That's the thing.
>> I don't have no bad
quarrels with nobody.
J.P., Brady, John and Brook--
they basically said, "Sarge,
we need to get rid of the
weakest link."
It's tricky to decide who I'm
going to vote for.
I said I'm going to think
about it.
They said the weakest link.
They're assuming that I agree
that the weakest link is Chris.
If we're going to stay in this--
the old people-- the only way
we're going get a million
dollars, one of us, is if we get
rid of the young people.
>> But J.P. is the only one that
really is trying to make fire.
I'd say Brook.
Brook is cocky, and we don't
know where he lies.
>> I'll talk to Chad.
I prepared to come here
mentally, and I prepared to
play the game.
I'm not vulnerable at all.
We got a plan.
>> I'm just trying to survive
the first couple days.
>> The one thing you got to
worry about is you never know.
Those guys could smarten up,
which I hope they didn't.
Personally, I think these are
all young guys on the team, guys
are going to be targets.
I feel like I am one of the
stronger, younger guys who's
going to be a target.
>> Right now, we're in
charge of...
As of right now, you know
what I mean?
>> Not necessarily.
>> Trust me.
>> Cool.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> All right, cool.
I'm down.
>> All right.
>> Well, obviously I haven't
fully made up my mind on who I'm
going to vote for yet tonight.
I'm thinking about Chris right
now, but Rory, he's kind of on
his own sheet of music a lot of
the time.
I think maybe some people feel
like Rory is maybe not putting
out as much group effort as some
of the other guys, and the group
right now is where it's all at.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
guys is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a touch,
approach a flame and get fire.
Because in this game, fire
represents your life.
As long as your torch has fire,
you're still in the game.
When your flame is gone,
so are you.
Welcome to your first Tribal
Council-- definitely not the
place you want to be.
Somebody is going to go home as
a result of today's loss.
But before we get to the vote,
let's talk about today's
challenge.
Anybody here willing to admit
that as they saw Chris fail,
fail, fail, that they started
thinking, "This guy is killing
us."
>> Oh, I mean, yeah.
Because it was so easy.
And I'm saying, "Come on, bring
your big tail across the doggone
beam.
We were ahead; now we're losing.
All we got to do is build a
little fire, blow the torch and
win over these females."
>> PROBST: Chris, at any point
while you're trying to cross it,
are you also thinking, "I'm
dead, I'm going home tonight"?
>> No, I wasn't.
I wasn't thinking "I'm going
home tonight."
I wasn't thinking "I'm dead."
I don't categorize stuff
like that.
The first night, Rory, he had
some ideas.
He was getting on people's
nerves.
Did I all of a sudden develop an
opinion about him and think,
"You know what?
He's going home the first time I
go to Tribal Council."
No, I didn't think that.
Everybody's going to help the
team some way, sometime down
along the line, and that's all I
think about.
>> PROBST: Rory, how are you
fitting in with this group?
>> I fit in fabulously well,
and I love my partners here.
We've accepted every single
thing that's come our way as a
family and as a team, and I
would expect that's the way
we're going to continue to
operate.
>> PROBST: J.P., how close are
you to crisis mode in terms of
not having water?
>> We're on red alert.
I mean, when you get into this
game, you realize, you take a
lot of things for granted, and
water is one of them.
You start getting headaches.
You can't get up.
You're lethargic.
You start cramping.
It's taken a toll on all of us
in some way or another.
>> PROBST: Before we get to the
vote, there's one other topic we
have to bring up.
You got your first look today at
the women.
>> Mmm.
>> PROBST: Bubba, that was just
a little grunt or a groan,
or a...?
>> Jeff, I've said it once,
I've said it a thousand times.
You never underestimate a woman.
I knew going into this that
these women were going to be
fighting hard, and I hope now
everybody respects these ladies,
'cause they mean business, and
they can kick our tail, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Brook, anybody you
wouldn't mind ending up on a
tribe with?
>> Yeah, there was a couple
girls that had really nice, um,
tails, but, uh, I was real
impressed with how competitive
some of those girls were.
It's one thing to expect it, and
one thing to see those girls
shimmying across that beam and
grinding their teeth and
screaming and yelling just
'cause they want to beat us
so bad.
But, yeah, I was peeking over
quite often when I got a chance.
>> PROBST: J.P., you had to be a
little surprised nine women
kicked your guys' butt.
>> I think as the group,
we expected to win.
Nine males, Jeff-- there's nine
of us.
We're all brute strong.
We're going to have to come in
and play the game a little bit
harder.
They just raised the level of
the game.
>> PROBST: With that, it is time
to vote.
Brook, you're up first.
>> Chris, I'm making this
vote to save my own butt, and
it's definitely strategy.
Good luck, bud.
>> If you get voted off
tonight, we'll miss your sage
comments around camp.
Right now, man, it's all about
team and winning.
>> I'm just playing the
game, man.
I started playing it when I got
to the beach.
It's all part of the game.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
The first vote.
Chris.
That's two votes Chris.
Rory.
Brook.
That's two votes Brook, two
votes Chris.
One vote Rory.
Chris.
Brook.
Three votes Brook,
three votes Chris.
One vote Rory.
Brook.
Four votes Brook,
three votes Chris.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu-- Islands of
Fire-- Brook.
You need to bring your torch.
Brook, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Three different tribe members
received votes.
You guys are going back to camp.
No water, no fire, 'cause you're
going to earn it or you're going
to build it.
You guys can head back to camp.
Good night.
>> Stay tuned for scenes from
our next episode.
>> Next time on Survivor:
Lines are drawn at Lopevi.
>> You are so friggin'
dangerous, man.
>> Who else is a threat?
>> PROBST: At Yasur, things
are bleak.
>> It's so miserable.
Being here is like being in
prison.
>> PROBST: And Rory gets mad.
>> That was nonsense.
That was classless.
>> I just don't think,
you know...
>> Show some class!
>> The one thing I didn't want
was to be the first person off.
Who the hell wants to be the
first person off?
But, uh, during these three days
in the game, I don't think I
have learned much about myself.
My only problem was, the other
17 people here just gave me an
absolute schooling in the game
of Survivor, so...
Uh, you know, I got beat.
The bottom line-- someone
got me. They got me good.
Peace out, Survivorland.