>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor:
There was a divide in the Yasur
tribe.
>> I definitely see groups
forming.
I think Lisa liked being in the
younger group and I think I
gravitate more towards the older
group.
>> PROBST: At Lopevi, John P.
also worried about the division
between the young and the old.
>> You're so friggin' dangerous,
man.
You're too big of a threat.
>> Right now, it's five against
three.
Those aren't good odds.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the tribes played for
a hammock, blankets and some
pillows.
Once again, the balance beam
proved to be a challenge for the
men and the women waltzed their
way to victory.
Yasur wins their second
challenge in a row.
Back at Lopevi, the women's
victory dance upset Rory.
>> I don't think we would
have intentionally shoved
somebody's nose into it.
That was classless.
>> It was a game.
I mean, we lost.
>> I understand it's a
competition, but if she was a
man, would you have taken that,
Sarge?
>> One person that's
striking me as wrong as rain.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Sarge lead Lopevi to
their first victory...
Lopevi wins immunity!
( cheering )
...giving them flint for fire.
Before Tribal Council, Dolly
couldn't commit to either group,
so she made deals to vote out
both Eliza and Leann.
>> I've got myself in a
cluster-you-know-what.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Twila pointed out the
differences in work ethic...
>> Leann, Scout and Ami,
us four did a lot of work.
>> PROBST: ...and Dolly's
indecision cost her the game.
Forced to save herself, Eliza
betrayed her group and voted
with the older women.
Dolly, the tribe has spoken.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( theme song playing )
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
( rumbling )
>> Dolly was totally
blindsided at Tribal Council
tonight.
She thought she was the one who
was the swing vote and she would
be the one deciding who went
home tonight, and, you know,
that's not how the chips fell,
so...
>> How the hell did the
vote switch to Dolly?
>> I think Mia and Julie
and Lisa are a little upset with
me right now, but I did what I
had to do to make sure I was
staying in this game.
I thought she was writing my
name down tonight.
She sat there and looked me in
the eye and said, "I'm going to
vote for a random person."
I... I couldn't get...
>> Hey, how about clueing
us in, Eliza?
>> I know, but when was
there time?
It was like you guys knew...
like you were off in the woods.
>> We thought Eliza was
strong with us, but I guess she
conspired with the other girls
and decided to vote off Dolly
without telling us.
So, yeah, we don't trust Eliza.
So Lisa and Julie are the only
girls I trust right now and I
guess we'll have to talk to
Eliza tomorrow and see where her
head was at on this, but we're
all very shocked right now.
>> We'll stack them.
You guys, like, free wrap it and
stack it and free wrap it...
and just keep crossing it so it
kind of binds as you go.
>> Uh-oh. Too short?
>> Too short.
>> Hmm.
Hey, where's Rory?
Is he okay?
>> Look at this!
Vitamin C!
Mm.
>> Hey, here comes Rory.
>> What's up?
>> When it comes to Rory,
the thing that really gets under
my skin is he doesn't do a lot
of, you know, physical work.
He's not a team player.
He's an individualist.
But in a team, you can't be your
own man all the time.
It has to be about the team.
Rory, I'm so used to supervising
40 people.
I see what everybody's doing.
I can't just sit here and do
what Sarge is doing.
>> Do you feel I'm not
pulling my weight?
>> I saw you go on a lot of
walks.
>> This is why I go on all my
>> Yeah. You found that?
That's cool.
>> Sarge wants to dictate
when people take a crap, when
people take a bath.
I'm a grown ass man and I don't
take orders real well.
Sarge, if you don't feel that
I'm pulling my weight, then you
come to me and say, "Rory, you
need to do a little more."
>> All I said was, "What is
he doing?"
You know, "people are really
working hard and he's going on
walks."
I had to hold back a lot of
comments and stuff, you know,
like...
>> And you think I haven't?
>> Rory has been very
opinionated and he's been
isolating himself from the
group.
Sarge is key in decision-making
for the five guys.
>> I'm hoping he'll say, "Hey,
maybe we should take J.P.
because we're having too
much conflict with one of the
guys in the main alliance."
>> Looks like it's going to
be a sunny day today.
We need to go on a serious food
hunt.
You want to go hunting for food
today?
Like, I want to seriously go
hunting for fruit.
>> How are people complaining
about people not doing work?
Somebody may be starting a fire,
but who's getting firewood?
Somebody might be doing the
shelter, but who's getting the
palm fronds? So, I...
>> No, honey. Just listen.
>> Last night was ridiculous.
> Am I on your side or what?
>> Now, wait a minute.
We've all asked you all...
>> Twila, we've done a ton of
work.
>> I'm not saying you didn't.
>> You start a fire in the
morning.
We could easily start that fire
in the morning if you were not
here.
You played it up last night, and
it's bull...
It's the card that you're
playing, and it's going to
backfire.
>> I'm not saying that
you all didn't do any work.
I said some do more than others.
>> Because you play the martyr
and you take on that role.
You take the martyr and you play
on that role.
If you were not here, we would
still have fire and shelter and
food.
That's it.
>> You stay here five
minutes, then your asses go
down there in the ocean, so
don't give me no bull, bitch,
because I will whip your butt.
>> It's your only card.
Keep playing it.
Bitch.
Twila and I were fighting about
the fact that she threw us all
under the bus last night, the
young'uns in the group, about
being lazy.
We've all pulled our weight
around here and I'm going to
call her out as much as
possible, because I can't stand
Twila-- I want her out.
>> No, you didn't say that.
You're lying.
If it's the damn truth, it would
be different, but you're damn
lying!
>> Whatever, Twila.
You play the martyr.
I don't care.
We all do our ... around here.
>> I didn't say everybody...
>> Yes, you did.
You called our asses out last
night.
>> Mia's mad because she knows I
was right.
Get off your ass and do
something.
Quit sitting on the beach and
going swimming when everybody
else's working.
Who was swimming down there...
>> Twila, because we were
swimming for ten minutes?
Who built this shelter?
Who got all the bamboo and the
palm fronds?
>> You honestly haven't seen...
>> Don't think you're going
to sit there and talk about me
and then today it's going to be
nice and lovey-dovey and kissy,
because you want to be fake.
>> I'm not going to sit
there and argue with her because
she's mad, but I ain't taking
her crap, I'll tell you that.
I'll whip the little scrawny
bitch's ass because I don't
care.
I ain't in it here to make no
friends.
>> So, what's up with you now?
Because everyone thinks you're
sketchy.
>> I feel like I am sketchy, but
I didn't ever make an alliance
with them.
I just said, "This time, we've
got to get rid of Dolly."
>> Okay, so there isn't like a
permanent thing going on?
>> No, no, no.
Julie and I went to get tree
mail and Julie was like, "Eliza,
are you still with us?"
And I was like, "I did what I
needed to do because, you know,
I didn't trust Dolly and I
thought that she was going to
vote for me."
>> Tree mail!
>> Oh, hey, you two.
Just the people we want to see.
>> Mia and Lisa walk up
to meet Julie and I, who are
coming back from getting tree
mail.
I'm with you 100%.
>> Okay.
>> I was like, "I'm with you
guys 100%."
>> Let's get rid of Twila.
I can't stand that bitch
anymore.
I'm about to bust ass.
Dude, Eliza, don't switch.
>> Please.
Please.
>> As long as the four of
us are still strong, we'll pull
somebody else in.
>> Well, I'm not so sure
that Eliza is in with us.
Even then, I don't know if I
trust her.
But I've got a backup plan, so
we'll see what happens.
>> Okay, ready?
"This next challenge is a tough
one.
Both tribes should feel quite
stressed.
The island's aura darkens.
Today, all friendships will be
put to the test.
A long day and night for
everyone.
Yes, there is need to worry."
>> Oh, no!
>> "With immunity on the
line, you better finish in a
hurry."
>> Immunity! Oh, my God!
>> Immunity, again?
Back-to-back ones?
>> We went to Tribal Council
last night and we have tree mail
talking about immunity.
And that bites because yesterday
sucked big time and I don't want
to go through it again two days
in a row.
>> PROBST: What's up, guys?
You look good.
>> Feel good, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Yasur, come on in!
Guys, get your first look at the
new Yasur tribe, minus one
member.
>> Who's gone, then?
>> PROBST: Dolly, voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
>> Dolly?
>> Dolly, the blonde.
>> Oh, Barbie's gone.
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first.
Chad, take back immunity.
Immunity back up for grabs.
Today, you are playing for both
reward and immunity.
( applause )
Here's the twist: both tribes
will vote out one member
tonight.
Separate Tribal Councils, two
people going home.
>> No!
>> PROBST: You'll first compete
tribe versus tribe for reward.
The winning tribe will then move
on and take part in an
individual immunity challenge
where one person will win
immunity.
They will be safe from the vote.
The losing tribe, they will go
to a separate Tribal Council.
They will vote out one member.
To be clear: two people going
home by the end of the day.
Okay, let me explain the reward
challenge.
You'll make your way through
three caged walls.
First wall, you're going to
untie a series of planks, get
yourself through a gate.
For the second wall, you'll use
grappling hooks, toss them out,
retrieve three rings with keys
from the sand.
Then open three locks, release
that gate, climb through.
For the third wall, you'll untie
a series of interlocking poles
until you can slide up the
center section, climb through.
First tribe to get all eight
members on their finish mat wins
reward and a shot at individual
immunity.
Big enough stakes?
>> Roger.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Want to know what the
reward is?
>> Yeah!
( applause )
>> PROBST: Fishing kit, Hawaiian
sling, mask, line, hooks...
>> That's what we want.
>> PROBST: ... and sinkers.
And today, what you covet:
Individual immunity for the
winner of the second phase of
the challenge.
Anything not clear?
Take your spots.
Wait for my go.
Here we go, for reward and a
shot at individual immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
>> Okay, this knot is important.
>> I got one off on the bottom.
>> Bottom board's loose from the
outside, guys.
>> PROBST: Two different
strategies.
>> Don't forget about the
inside ropes.
>> PROBST: Lopevi really spread
out; they have a plan.
Yasur all grouped together.
They have a plan.
>> I got this one.
>> The lower ones, guys.
Lower.
>> Yes, I got this one.
>> Work with me on the outside,
guys.
>> PROBST: Guys are on their
final knot.
>> Start doing it.
One will do. One will do.
>> Right there.
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Lopevi's through to
the second wall.
Let's go, Yasur.
You're moving slow.
>> Watch out.
Watch out for this one.
>> PROBST: Bubba and J.P.
with the hooks, looking for
three keys.
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> There you go! There you go!
>> Yeah, baby!
>> PROBST: Easy, easy, easy.
>> You can't jerk it.
>> PROBST: Bubba had one and he
lost it.
>> What about this one?
We can go?
>> PROBST: Yasur getting
through.
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: You're in this, guys.
Let's go!
>> Now really chuck it.
>> Right there.
>> PROBST: J. P.'s got a ring
hooked.
>> Swing it over. Over.
>> Try again. Try again, honey.
>> PROBST: Scout with a short
toss; that's not going to work.
>> Just a little bit faster.
Pull it straight. I got it.
>> There it is.
There's one! There's one!
>> PROBST: J.P. has his first
key for Lopevi.
>> There you go, all right!
Pull from here.
>> PROBST: Yasur's hooked a
ring.
>> Good job, Twila.
>> PROBST: Twila pulling that
ring in.
She's got it hooked.
Yasur has their first key.
>> Aim past it, dude.
He's got it. He's got it.
>> PROBST: J. P.'s got another
one.
>> Take your time, J.P.
Take your time, buddy.
>> Get ready, get ready, get
ready.
Get ready. All right!
>> PROBST: Lopevi with their
second key.
One more to go.
>> Aw!
>> PROBST: Lopevi's lost one of
their grappling hooks.
Yasur going for their second
key.
>> You're on fire, Scout.
>> PROBST: Scout, you going to
throw that thing or dance with
it?
>> Come on, guys, faster.
Let's throw it.
>> I got one.
>> I got it.
>> Wait! Go slow, because we
could get a key.
>> Come on, quick, quick!
>> PROBST: Leann and Twila
working together.
They've got another one.
Yasur's tied it up.
>> Okay, okay, okay.
>> PROBST: Lopevi trying to get
their grappling hook back,
pulling it in.
>> Scout, come on!
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Another short toss by
Scout.
>> I got it!
>> You got it, got it, got it.
Bring it, bring it, bring it.
>> Got it, got it.
Here, here, here.
>> PROBST: Lopevi has their last
key.
Yasur still needs one more.
>> Go for another one.
Go for another one.
>> Got it, got it!
>> Got it. Let's go. Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Lopevi's got all the
locks they need and they are
through.
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Moving on to the last
gate.
Let's go, Yasur.
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: Twila pulling in
Yasur's last key.
>> Here, key!
Right here, right here.
Right here.
>> Come on, guys.
>> Pull that one out.
>> PROBST: Sarge removing a
pole.
>> Pull it out!
>> PROBST: John removing a pole.
>> Oh, we're good.
>> Don't! Get off!
What are you doing? Go through!
>> PROBST: Sarge barking out
orders.
>> Don't step on that!
>> PROBST: Brady throwing tribe
members through.
>> Guys, I got it, I got it!
>> Right over here, Twila!
Twila!
>> PROBST: And here comes Sarge
bringing up the caboose.
>> Lopevi!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Lopevi wins reward
and a shot at individual
immunity!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Yasur, take a seat on
the mat.
You'll be sitting this next
challenge out.
All right, Lopevi,
congratulations.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: You now have a
Hawaiian sling, fishing gear and
a mask.
You're also going to take part
in an individual immunity
challenge.
Here's how it works.
Buried in each of these lanes
are seven ladder rungs.
Your job: to dig up the rungs,
put your ladder together.
Keep in mind, each rung is
unique and will not fit in every
slot.
First person to put their ladder
together correctly and get to
the top wins immunity.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Take a spot.
Wait for my go.
Here we go, guys.
At stake: individual immunity,
ensuring your safety at
tonight's Tribal Council.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Brady trying to figure out how
deep they are.
Sarge has his first piece.
So does Chad.
John, there's his first.
Brady on the board.
Bubba, I don't know what he's
looking for.
( laughter )
Chad has two.
Rory putting his feet to work
digging.
John with another piece.
( cheers )
Bubba finally on the board.
( laughter )
Chad digging into that sand,
finds another one.
John with five.
Chad with six, looking for
seven.
Chris with another piece, up to
five.
Only two shy.
Chad has his seventh piece.
He's got to start putting his
puzzle together.
John has his seventh piece.
Going to start putting his
ladder together.
Remember, guys, this is a
puzzle.
Each rung only fits one way into
the ladder.
Chad's got another piece.
John with another piece.
Chad with five.
J.P. with his seventh piece.
He's putting his ladder
together.
Chad trying to find out which
piece is not right.
John working on his last piece.
He's got it.
John wins immunity!
>> Good job, John.
>> PROBST: Came from behind.
Nice job.
Congratulations.
You're safe at tonight's Tribal
Council.
There's one other thing.
Come on down.
>> One other thing.
>> PROBST: John, you're now
going to leave and go back to
camp with Yasur.
Join them.
( laughter and applause )
>> Whoo!
>> Welcome.
>> PROBST: Now, before you get
too excited, it's not forever.
You're going to go back to Camp
Yasur.
You'll be gathering information
for a very big decision, because
tonight you will return to
Tribal Council where you will
meet Lopevi.
You guys will have your own
Tribal Council.
You'll be safe.
One of these guys is going home.
When your tribal is over, you
will stay behind.
Yasur comes in.
You will give your immunity to
one member from Yasur.
You're not to discuss who you
are giving your immunity to.
You'll keep that a secret until
we get to Tribal Council.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Head on out, guys.
>> Because I won the
immunity challenge, I can't get
voted off tonight.
But, strangely, there was a
little twist and I got a chance
to meet the women, see their
camp, and then pick one that can
have the necklace for their
Tribal Council.
So, who knows what's going to
happen tonight with both tribes
voting people off?
It could really change the
dynamics of both groups, big
time.
Everyone that voted for Dolly,
raise your hand.
All right.
You guys, this way.
>> When we hit the beach,
John immediately made a stand.
It's like, "Girls who voted for
Dolly over here and girls who
voted for Leann over here,"
which made no sense.
What does it matter?
I thought it was completely
ridiculous.
>> All right, guys.
Check it out.
>> All right, these four
guys were planning on voting me
out last night.
>> Take that back.
>> Wait a minute, wait a
minute.
>> Okay, okay, okay.
I didn't want John thinking that
this was some five-person
alliance, because that's
definitely not what it was.
I felt like I needed to explain
to him that it was because my
head was on the chopping block.
I go, "Dolly, look me in the eye
and tell me you're not writing
my name down."
She's like, "I don't know.
I don't want to vote with either
side.
I'm just going to vote for
someone random."
And I go, "Oh, she's voting
against me."
And then, it was like...
>> She was trying to play both
sides.
>> Yeah, she was.
>> It was a few...
>> JOHN: And she got caught.
>> Yeah.
>> It was a few hours
before Tribal Council and Dolly
goes...
>> That's all I need to know,
yeah.
>> I'm just going to go talk to
them.
>> She went up there and she
goes...
>> I'm just going to go talk to
them.
>> There's no way he's
giving her immunity, you know?
>> He's not going to give
any of them immunity.
>> Unless he wants to...
>> Good, Eliza, keep
talking.
Dig yourself in a hole, Eliza.
Stupid.
>> Yeah, and she won't let
anybody else talk.
>> I know, please.
>> Yesterday, after we
lost the immunity challenge, if
you would have looked at me, I
was crying.
It was so sad.
Like, we all get along so well.
Like, really, it's been amazing.
>> Mm-hmm.
Eliza just didn't stop talking.
She just kept talking and
talking and talking.
I mean, she seems really sweet.
I'm sure she's really nice, but
the bottom line is, "Oh, my God,
would you please stop talking?"
Hi, I'm John.
>> Mia.
>> JOHN: Nice to meet you.
>> I'm Lisa.
>> Julie.
>> JOHN: Nice to meet you.
All right, here's my question:
flat out, who do you guys think
you need to get off?
>> Just don't give it to
Twila, please.
>> JOHN: No, I won't give it to
Twila.
>> Please.
>> Or Eliza.
>> JOHN: The girls told me not
to give the immunity necklace to
Eliza and Twila, but I could
care less who gets voted off of
this tribe.
I just want them to not be mad
at me for whoever gets voted
off, because I might merge with
them and it would be nice to
have them on my side later on.
>> Here she comes.
She's going to work us now.
>> Oh, no, tell her to go away.
Whoa, this is our time.
>> Have you guys found any
grubs?
>> No.
>> So, what's up with you?
>> Yeah, dude, what's up?
Teetering?
>> I am not teetering.
>> You're not voting for me
tonight.
>> No way in hell.
Scout is a detriment in
challenges.
>> I don't want to vote for
Scout.
>> She thinks we can't...
>> I don't want to vote
for Scout.
>> I do.
>> I don't.
If it goes five-three?
>> I would rather vote for
Twila than Scout.
>> Then it would be a tie for
me.
>> I don't know what's
going on with them, I just know
they are not too happy with each
other.
To see some conflict like that,
it's going to fun to pick a girl
to not get voted off.
>> You just keep saying you
don't want there to be a tie,
well...
>> I know...
Honestly, I don't trust you,
Eliza.
>> Shh, let's not do this
right now.
>> Fine, don't trust me.
Fine, fine, because I'm going to
be the first one out anyhow.
You've been mad at me since I
voted for Dolly and I understand
why, but, like...
>> I'm over it.
>> Me, too.
>> I just want to know what's up
tonight.
>> Eliza, if we can get rid
of one of them tonight, it's us
four strong again, and they're
out.
Eliza seems to be teetering a
little bit, but tonight at
Tribal Council I'm almost
positive it's going to be a tie.
I mean, me and Twila had one of
our famous fights this morning,
so I think that me and Julie and
Lisa and Eliza are going to be
voting for Twila, and I'm pretty
sure that Leann and Ami and
Twila and Scout will be voting
for me tonight.
But, there's still individual
immunity to be given out, too,
so I don't know what's going to
happen.
>> Man, we kicked ass
on those rings, didn't we?
Man, oh, man.
We won the reward challenge.
It was a great feeling.
And then, after that, we ran
into the immunity challenge.
Out of most of the other guys, I
needed it the most, so I think
that I'm going to be quite
vulnerable tonight.
I would actually like to use the
term "dead man walking."
Brady's in the same boat.
We're the youngest guys there.
We're the strongest there.
And right now, it's five against
three.
We've got to plant the seed in
Sarge's head, saying, "Sarge,
ally with us or think about
getting rid of Rory," because
the Sarge and Rory are the last
few days have been having some
conflict.
What about this idea of after
the merge?
You need the group of guys that
you think, if they hang
together, will be the last
people in the game.
>> Right.
>> If one of the four of us can
win most of the challenges, we
just look out for each other and
we make sure we're the last
four.
>> It's possible.
It's possible.
>> It's simple.
It's not underhanded.
And we know our four votes are
going in one direction.
>> I don't know.
I got a real bad feeling about
one of our pact, man.
He's just got a sorry attitude.
>> You don't have to
worry about no one in our pact,
I guarantee you that.
>> No, I ain't... I'm not
worried about that.
I have trouble working next to
him and being around him right
now.
>> Rory?
>> Yeah!
I'm like...
I mean...
>> Dude, I understand
what you're saying, and we'll
deal with it, but this just
isn't the time.
>> I hate Tribal Council.
I hate building a team of men or
survivors, building them up to a
fine-tuned team and then tearing
them down.
That's not me.
But I'm playing this game, and
during this game I have to do
that.
>> PROBST: Bring in John.
He spent the afternoon over at
the Yasur camp.
I'm sure you had an interesting
afternoon.
>> Yes, I did.
>> PROBST: We'll get to that in
a minute.
First, though, I want to talk
about the tribe.
Chad, how have you seen this
tribe change and grow?
>> We've had camaraderie
since the very get-go, and I
think that we've gained a lot of
confidence by winning some of
the challenges, and that's
brought us closer together.
>> PROBST: Brady, any first
impressions here that have
changed?
>> I don't know if it's
better or worse, but I certainly
had a different impression of
Sarge.
Sarge is kind of a loud, booming
personality, but Sarge is a much
more personable guy than most
people would probably give him
credit for and that most people
see.
>> PROBST: So, John, while these
guys are back at camp, you're
over with the women.
How aggressive were the women in
terms of working you for that
thing around your neck,
immunity?
>> You know what, as
soon as I went in there, I said,
"people who voted for Dolly," I
said, "go over there.
People who didn't vote for
Dolly, go over there."
And as soon as I divided them, I
figured out what their alliances
were, and it was really easy
after I divided them.
>> Good job.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Who knew young John
was this bright?
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: So you feel very
confident in the decision you're
making?
>> I feel 150% confident.
>> PROBST: Now, let's get to
this vote.
J. P, what are you basing your
vote on?
>> I think you want
this group as strong as possible
going into that next challenge.
Who are those individuals that
have the particular strengths,
the skill-sets, the mesh, the
personality that can move
forward and prepare for that
merge?
>> PROBST: Sarge, tough vote for
you, or is this easy because
friendship isn't part of this
game?
>> Friendships...
I have
friendships here, but I'm here
to play a game.
The person going home tonight is
a casualty of war.
>> PROBST: Okay, it's time to
vote.
John, you're wearing the
immunity necklace.
You're the only person safe.
Everybody else is fair game.
John, you're up first.
>> I'm voting for you.
I might be weaker than you
physically, but I'm stronger
than you mentally.
It's just a game.
>> Ain't nothing personal, man.
I'm just being consistent.
>> I'm voting for Rory
tonight because you are the
weakest guy in the tribe.
Hopefully, there will be four
votes to get you out.
Or tie with me.
>> This is our strategy.
Sorry, my friend.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Rory.
J. P.
That's two votes J.P.
Rory.
Two votes Rory; two votes J.P.
Three votes Rory; two votes
J.P.
Tied.
Three votes J P.
Three votes Rory.
Four votes J.P.
Last vote.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu, J.P.
Please bring me your torch.
J. P., the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, both times, you guys have
been to Tribal Council, the
consensus has been that the vote
was based on keeping the tribe
strong.
You voted out two of your
strongest members.
Interesting strategy.
See if it works.
John, you'll stay behind for the
next Tribal Council.
The rest of you guys take your
torches with you back to camp.
Good night.
>> Well, what can I say?
I survived seven days.
I was hoping to stay a little
bit longer, but there's no way
that I think I was outwitted,
outlasted, outplayed.
Coming to the island and being
part of something that I
couldn't even imagine, I'll tell
you, what an experience.
>> PROBST: Welcome back to
Tribal Council.
Lopevi has already voted
somebody out.
John is staying behind because,
as you know, he's going to award
one of you his immunity necklace
which will make you safe from
the vote tonight.
You know who you're going to
give it to?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: So, Yasur, one of you
is about to become immune from
the vote.
John, give it up.
Why Ami?
>> Because, out of
everyone there, she was not
getting voted off tonight no
matter what-- and I think you
guys need to figure out who you
want to vote out.
And because I picked her, it's
probably going to be who it was
going to be anyway, and you'll
figure out a lot about your own
tribe, because you guys are two
sides.
Grab your torch...
>> Take it easy, guys.
>> PROBST: ... find the rest of
your tribe.
>> Bye, John.
>> PROBST: Good night.
Ami, surprised?
>> A little surprised, yeah.
I thought that he would put it
on someone's head that he
thought might get voted out
tonight.
>> PROBST: Scout, you leave here
after a very surprising vote to
a lot of people.
You go back to camp.
It's a tough night.
You get up in the morning, and
what happens?
>> It was obvious that
Mia was a little pissed off at
the vote, didn't understand it.
This morning, when they got up,
Twila and Mia really got into
it.
>> PROBST: Mia, what's your
take?
>> It had nothing really to
do about the vote.
It just had to do about Twila's
comments about the young ones
not doing anything, not pulling
their weight.
And it really did upset me, so I
confronted her about it this
morning.
>> PROBST: Twila, did you make a
comment about workload?
>> She was offended by
what I said last night at Tribal
Council.
I don't know why I offended her
so bad, but I just said what I
felt.
I felt like I was telling the
truth.
>> PROBST: Julie, what's the
result of that?
>> I think it goes a
little deeper than the comment.
Speaking for myself, I haven't
felt like Twila's made any
effort to communicate or build
anything with me, so, you know,
without that bridge, it's
frustrating, and I think Mia got
frustrated.
>> They haven't given me
an opportunity to talk to them.
I mean, why would I want to walk
up to somebody that rolls their
eyes at me all the time and acts
like they can't stand to be
around me?
Why would I even want to try?
>> Twila, you talk to me in
one-word answers.
I'm not going to try to pull a
conversation out of you.
>> That's just my
personality, and that's just how
I am.
>> You have plenty of
conversations with everybody
else except for a couple of us.
>> I just communicate
better with men than I do women.
I always have, always will.
I am the tomboy.
I do weld.
I do fix trucks.
I do those things.
And it's hard for me to bring up
conversation with these women
that I feel I have nothing in
common with.
You know, until you walk in
somebody else's shoes, don't
judge.
>> Have you taken the time
to walk in these girls' shoes
and realize they're just girls?
They like to play on the beach.
They like to do girly stuff.
Like, have you taken that time?
>> No, I haven't.
I'll be honest with you.
I haven't.
>> Do you realize that
right now is your opportunity
to, like, find the feminine side
of you and just let go of "this
is what I am" and realize
there's so much more to you than
just that?
There is a wonderful,
feminine...
>> Maybe I don't have a
feminine side to me, I don't
know.
>> Yes, you do.
Just say, "you know what?
Will you guys French-braid my
hair tomorrow?
Will one of you French..."
you know?
Something silly like that.
I know, it sounds crazy.
Give it a go.
It feels nice to have someone
else French-braid your hair.
>> I can try that.
We can start with the hair.
That'd be working.
Even do my nails, too, while
you're at it, would you?
Yeah, that'd be great.
That'd be great.
>> PROBST: Scout, what are you
basing your vote on tonight?
>> Maintaining a healthy,
emotional attitude in camp.
>> PROBST: Your vote tonight is
to get rid of somebody that you
think is causing disharmony,
chaos, problems.
>> Yeah, chaos, agitation,
disharmony, yeah.
>> PROBST: Mia, you're shaking
your head, rolling your eyes,
closing your eyes.
You're like the little doggie in
the window.
>> I feel like Scout's
statement is definitely pointed
toward me and the disharmony was
our fight today.
And I think it was on both
sides, so I don't see where I'm
causing emotional distress in
the tribe at all.
>> PROBST: Eliza, decided who
you're voting for?
>> I think Scout's
statement about disharmony is a
good one, but if I had the
choice to keep everyone here I
definitely would.
>> PROBST: With that, it is time
to vote.
Ami is the only person you
cannot vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
Mia, you're up.
>> Twila, I'm voting for you.
You said you can't relate to
women, and, unfortunately, you
got stuck on an all women's
tribe.
I don't want to spend another
day on the island with you.
>> Mia, your volcano
erupts more than I like.
Good luck in finding a husband
that will put up with you.
>> I think you're a young
woman that's got a big chip on
her shoulder.
I think that you got a mouth-
and-a-half and I think you need
to go.
That's all.
>> Twila, my vote's for you.
I think you have an amazing work
ethic, but you can't be here
anymore.
Sorry.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Twila.
Mia.
One vote Twila; one vote Mia.
Twila.
Two votes Twila; one vote Mia.
Mia.
Two votes Mia; two votes Twila.
That's three votes Mia; two
votes Twila.
Twila.
You're tied.
Three votes Twila; three votes
Mia.
That's four votes Mia; three
votes Twila.
One vote left.
The fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu, Mia.
Bring me your torch.
Mia, the tribe has spoken.
>> Thanks.
Kick ass, ladies.
>> Bye, Mia.
>> PROBST: Well, if there was
one clear theme from tonight's
Tribal Council, it was that the
seven of you desire to be a
strong group of women with
emotional harmony.
The question is: did tonight's
vote bring you any closer?
Ami, you can leave that necklace
behind.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor,
at Lopevi, Brady tries to turn
the tide.
>> If I can endear myself
with the fishing, that may
change people's minds.
>> Give it a chance to grow up.
>> PROBST: At Yasur, old allies
become new enemies.
>> I didn't trust you.
I had a right, and I changed my
mind.
I'm not going to be
confrontational.
>> That bitch.
>> I've met a lot of
amazing girls and a lot of
people that I'd like to never
see again, one of those being
Twila.
Um, Twila, you have been
extremely deceiving with all the
girls.
I thought you were absolutely
horrendous to me, and I think
that you did not have the social
skills to play this game at all,
and that's going to wear on the
girls, um, and hopefully you'll
get voted off next.