>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor:
At Lopevi, the tribe had enough
of John's lazy attitude.
>> He's the kind of person that
coasts through the game.
>> Yeah, he is.
>> He's not coasting
through this game with us.
>> No.
>> At Yasur, Rory attempted
to break into Ami and Leann's
alliance.
>> I need to know where you guys
stand with regards to me.
>> What happens when the
merger comes with the men?
>> I don't give a ...
about them men.
I know you guys a lot better
than I know them.
>> Unfortunately for you,
the fact that the women had this
alliance excludes you.
>> At the reward challenge,
Lopevi got an unexpected
surprise.
Lisa voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> I thought for sure that they
would have gotten rid of him,
keep the women together.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready, go!
After a nerve-wracking challenge
that tested the survivors'
steadiness, it was Yasur that
walked away with victory.
Yasur wins Home Cafe reward.
And a little taste of home.
>> Whoa!
>> Guys, look, pictures.
Me and my sisters.
>> Oh.
>> This is our first Halloween
together.
>> Oh.
>> Coffee, croissants,
and we got letters from home.
>> To love and to family.
>> PROBST: Though emotions
brought the tribe together...
>> I'm really happy right now.
>> PROBST: ...Rory kept his
guard up.
>> Even though this is a
loving moment, and we're
bonding, I ain't forgot where
they put me.
>> PROBST: At Lopevi...
>> Would you like to join me?
>> PROBST: ...Twila and Julie
plotted to stick together and
keep their options open.
>> I don't have any
loyalties to the women.
>> I don't, either.
>> I just think the guys are
gonna shaft us whenever they
get a chance, but little do they
know...
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Rory knew he had to
come through, and he did,
sparing himself and his tribe
mates a trip to Tribal Council.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Yasur wins immunity!
( cheering )
>> Whoa. Whoa!
>> PROBST: Back at camp, there
were mixed emotions over the
win.
>> I'm really glad that we
won, but at the same time, I
looked over at Lopevi, and it
hurt to know that either Julie
or Twila are going home tonight.
>> PROBST: At Lopevi, John was
on the chopping block until Chad
questioned Julie's loyalty.
>> I'm not comfortable
with Julie staying with us,
dude.
>> Well...
>> If we merge, she's gonna go
right with the women.
>> PROBST: And John targeted
Chad.
>> Chad-- he gets the sympathy
vote, and if it ever came down
to him and one of us in the
final two, he'd get it in
a heartbeat.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Julie and Twila dodged
the vote when the guys trusted
the women's loyalty and voted
out John.
John, the tribe has spoken.
Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( theme song playing )
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> We stay five, we're solid.
We go to the end.
>> What happened at Tribal was
a wonderful thing...
( laughs )
...'cause I thought I was going
home.
Temporarily, I'm still here, so
I'm psyched.
>> Are you sure you guys
don't want any manioc?
>> I'm good.
>> I don't want any, and
I'm-I'm fine.
>> We're sitting around the
fire, and Julie just sits down
between my legs and-and gets
warm.
And I was like, whoa.
>> Really good.
>> You know what's going
to be so satisfying?
The women seeing us.
>> Oh, definitely.
>> Yeah, they're gonna
know we're with you guys.
>> I thought it was interesting
at first, but no big deal, she's
cold.
But then, once the fire started
blazing, she just stayed there
and kind of snuggled in closer,
and Sarge was just kind of
letting it happen.
( laughter )
>> You see that?
>> I know.
When she snuggled up with you?
>> I was, like, that's hot.
>> I know, man.
>> She's just wanting to
solidify another three days.
>> Totally, man.
>> Sure.
>> Like, remember Ginger
on Gilligan's Island?
>> Yeah.
>> Hello.
>> Oh, hell, yes, Julie is using
her sex appeal and her young age
and her body, trying to get next
to the men.
There's no doubt about it.
Not much I can do about it.
She's 22 years younger than I
am.
>> You know, Julie's fine,
she's hot, you know?
She's a model.
I mean, I really don't hang out
with too many young, 22-year-old
models, you know?
>> Do it.
>> You're not offending me.
Bare the ass.
>> Julie is, like, "You
know, you look good.
You ought to expose your body
some more."
And I said, "What the hell?"
>> I see it.
( Twila laughs )
>> Yeah, that's a white ass.
>> Ow, that's a white ass.
We all three ought to do it and
slide next to Sarge.
( Twila laughs )
>> Mine's white, too.
>> Julie is an exhibitionist.
I mean, she's comfortable with
it.
And I told 'em, I'm comfortable
with it, because I've been in
Europe.
>> Uno, dos, tres.
>> Ah!
>> Sarge...
( Twila laughs )
>> Sarge, what are you doing?
>> What are you doing?
>> I just glanced over there.
Sarge has his ass hanging out.
Probably is an image that will
never leave my memory.
Julie is a bad influence!
( laughter )
>> Oh.
>> Seriously, there is
nothing going through my mind
of, like, this is going to keep
me solid, but, hey, if those
boys want to keep me around
strictly for visual stimulation,
well then, hey, I got it in the
bag then, right?
( cawing )
( screeching )
( birds singing )
>> If Scout and I stopped
working, this camp literally
would stop.
Leann and Ami and Eliza should
be disgusted with themselves.
Their main activity for the day
consists of waking up late and
then sitting on their asses for
the rest of the day, and I'm
tired of it.
( Ami sighs )
>> Is coffee ready to go?
>> I don't know, but it's
starting to really hurt to
sleep.
>> Leann gets up, and
she's a little crabby.
She's got coffee right there,
she's got water boiled, and
she's got plantains ready to
eat, and she's crabby.
>> Rory, you'd better get over
here and get some of the
breakfast you cooked.
>> Yeah, I'll be over
there in a second.
>> Wait.
All that water?
Yuck.
>> You don't like the water?
>> Uh-uh. No.
>> Yeah.
>> That doesn't taste
good at all.
>> What a worthless crew.
What a completely worthless
crew.
Stupid people irritate the
living hell out of me.
Eliza-- she's like a little kid.
>> All right.
Let's try and move the fire.
>> I have personally taught
Eliza at least four or five
times how to make a fire.
Come over on the side and push
everything that way.
And she's still struggling with
boiling a pot of water!
>> I don't know how it
was... earlier.
>> And I think Ami is just
taking advantage of everybody.
Ami is just riding her little
queen role, and I'd really like
to knock her ass down a peg,
quite frankly.
I'm ready to get the hell out of
Yasur.
I really, really, really want to
be around some men.
I'm tired of these women.
I'm tired of 'em.
>> PROBST: Yasur, getting your
first look at the new Lopevi
tribe.
John voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
( sigh )
>> PROBST: What was that
reaction for, Scout?
>> I'm just so happy to see
Twila.
I had a dream last night that
Twila had to go home, and she
was crying, and I was crying,
and...
Whoo!
Yeah!
>> Twila ain't going nowhere.
>> PROBST: Scout, Sarge clearly
took that as a sign that you
think Twila is part of a women's
tribe.
>> Well, he can think
whatever he wants to think.
I'm just glad to see her.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: It is for reward, and
you're going to get wet.
You're going to compete tribe
versus tribe in a relay-style
race.
Each tribe member will take a
spot at one of five stations.
The first tribe member will pick
up a bucket, race down to the
ocean, fill it with water, race
back to the mat.
They will then toss the bucket
with the water in it to the
second tribe member who will
toss it to the third tribe
member who will toss it to the
fourth tribe member.
That person will take whatever
water is left in the bucket,
while holding onto the bucket,
toss just the water to the fifth
tribe member.
They will race up the ladder,
put the water in the final
bucket on the fire tower.
Once you fill that fire tower
bucket with water, it will
lower, the flame will rise,
lighting a fuse, igniting the
tower.
The first tribe to ignite the
tower wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> ALL: Yeah.
>> PROBST: Day 19, taste buds
still working, but it's been a
while.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: So we thought we
might have a little dessert.
>> Oh! Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: So we have some ice
cold milk.
>> Oh.
>> And?
>> Jeff... Chris.
>> Chris' milk.
( Julie laughs )
>> PROBST: You're a milk lover?
>> I'm a milk lover.
>> PROBST: What goes with milk?
>> Cookies.
>> PROBST: Chocolate chip
cookies.
( cheering )
>> Oh, my God.
>> All the chocolate
chips and milk we can eat.
>> PROBST: But it is day 19.
I feel like I ought to go see if
there's something else to
complete this dessert.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> What else you got?
>> Oh, God, it's big.
>> PROBST: For one tribe,
with the milk and the cookies,
comes this.
( cheering )
( laughter )
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: Figure out your
strategy, wait for my go.
For ice cold milk, cookies and
one of the biggest chocolate
cakes I've ever seen, survivors
ready.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Go.
>> Go, Sarge.
>> Go, Eliza!
>> PROBST: Eliza and Sarge
in the water.
Here comes the first tosses.
>> You guys, you guys.
>> Nice and easy.
>> Nice.
>> PROBST: Yasur loses almost
everything on their first toss.
>> Nothing.
>> PROBST: Scout really taking
her time.
( indistinct chatter )
And it doesn't help.
Rory with only drops.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Good toss by Julie.
Chris still waiting for
something to dump.
>> Ah.
>> PROBST: Ami goes high and
gives Rory a bath.
>> Don't try to stop it on
your body, Twila.
Don't stop it on your body.
>> PROBST: Sarge getting
irritated with his troop.
Somebody is going to be running
laps for Lopevi.
Here comes the critical toss.
Chris gets a little water this
time.
Oh.
( Jeff laughs )
>> Eliza you're doing great.
>> PROBST: Eliza to Leann who
tosses to Scout and goes to Ami
into Rory.
Rory catches a lot.
>> That's it right there.
That's it, boys.
There you go.
>> Here you go.
Guys, use your shirt.
You can wring your shirt out in
it.
>> PROBST: It's fair game.
Everybody's using their clothing
items.
>> Let's go, Lopevi.
>> PROBST: Scout to Ami.
And Rory bounces it off his
chest, squeezing his shorts.
Every drop counts.
( indistinct chatter )
>> There you go.
There you go, that's it.
>> PROBST: Twila to Julie.
A lot of water in that bucket.
Chad, nice catch.
They've got a full bucket.
Chad and Chris getting their act
together.
>> That's it.
>> PROBST: Yasur still looks to
have a slight lead.
Lopevi getting closer.
>> Good one, dude.
That was a good throw.
>> PROBST: Yasur right behind.
>> Come on, you guys.
We are close.
>> I got to just...
>> PROBST: Ami and Rory still
struggling.
>> Good job...
Nice...
>> PROBST: He's emptying his
shoe, he's wearing so much
water.
>> Use your buff.
( Lea speaking quietly )
>> PROBST: Twila to Julie.
Nice catch.
Another nice toss to Chad, and
Chris gets a lot of it.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Scout to Ami.
They've got a good bucketful.
How much will go in?
Not enough.
( cheering )
Lopevi extending their lead.
Wow.
A lot of water on that last
round for Lopevi.
>> We're moving.
We are moving.
Come on.
>> PROBST: That bucket's
starting to move for Lopevi.
Yasur better pick it up.
>> Go, Sarge.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Lopevi with a great
system.
Working together well.
>> Come on...
>> Come on.
( indistinct chatter )
>> CHAD: Ready.
>> PROBST: Chad and Chris.
It's working.
Rory and Chris both heading
back up.
Both have water.
>> Yeah, Chris, way to climb.
>> PROBST: First one to light
the tower wins reward.
Lopevi is moving.
That may be enough.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: And it is.
Lopevi wins reward.
( cheering )
Yasur, good effort.
You've been on a winning streak.
It ends today.
Head back to camp.
Lopevi, you are back.
>> We are back.
>> PROBST: Your reward is
waiting for you right here.
Your responsibility to get
it back to camp.
>> How heavy is it?
I hope it's very heavy.
>> Hey, the whole cake is there.
>> There's so much left.
>> All I know right now is
I don't want to... see no
chocolate cake.
Just the thought of it makes me
sick to my stomach right now.
I wish yesterday's challenge
never even happened because I
guess my body just wasn't ready
for some sugar.
It made me feel so awful.
>> After all that chocolate
yesterday, I thought I'd my fill
a little bit, but no way.
Last night, we just kicked butt.
>> I knew when she started
talking like that, I thought,
"Oh, thanks, Scout."
Scout made a few comments last
night at the game, she just kept
on and on about me and I'm going
"Scout, shut up," you know,
because I need these guys to
believe that I'm wholeheartedly
on their side and here she is
going on about how she missed me
and how she said a prayer for me
and she was so glad to see me
and yadda, yadda, yadda.
And hell, yeah, them guys'd be
stupid if they didn't read
something into that last night.
>> I don't think we've
got much to worry about.
Julie's security is right here.
She proved that in Tribal
Council.
>> And with Twila, she's too
stubborn to go with those women.
>> She's not going.
>> Nah.
This morning, I had a
conversation with Chris about
this sort of, you know, unity in
our pact, and we decided to go
one step further.
>> Do you want to do the
one I want or do you have
something with Sarge already?
>> Sarge has never said
"let's go to the end together."
>> Sarge would be a hell of a
choice to take to the final
two because he would win.
>> I'm going to be honest
with you, I think both of you
got a leg up on me.
Dude, I didn't mean to say that.
>> No, I...
>> Totally, dude.
>> Listen, no.
There's so many puns, dude.
There's a million.
>> God, I didn't just say that.
I'm pretty much covering all
my bases.
Covering all my bases means I'll
be good any way it goes.
And the final two.
>> All right, man.
>> Hey.
I threw my hand out.
It's just me reassuring my
position in the game because
basically I have the same
agreement with Sarge, and I've
pretty much made the same
agreement with Julie.
So, okay, let's say we merge, do
you want to stick together and
watch out for each other or not?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, if you're not
comfortable doing it...
If you don't trust me, all
you've got to do is tell me.
I understand that.
>> No.
>> Maybe I'm going places
I shouldn't be going, but if we
merge, Julie could go, Sarge
could go, Chad could go.
I'm always going to have two
others I can rely on to watch
my back.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
All right.
Shall we get to the challenge?
Take back immunity.
What happened to the immunity
idol?
>> They broke its neck.
>> I went to stick it in
the ground and he snapped.
>> PROBST: So the immunity idol
is broken, which is just as
well, because we don't need
it anymore.
>> Uh-oh.
>> PROBST: Drop your buffs.
Buffs, drop 'em.
>> God.
>> PROBST: Take 'em off.
Drop them at your feet.
You're now one tribe.
>> Whoo!
>> Hi, Sarge.
>> PROBST: All right, guys, one
big decision to make right now.
Which beach are you going to
live on?
>> The guys, they've got
an excellent place.
The beach is a lot closer and
it's better and there's a big
fire up on the hill.
>> Let's go to the guys.
>> PROBST: Lopevi is the beach?
>> Lopevi.
>> PROBST: So all of Yasur's
personal items, all your reward
items, everything you have will
be waiting for you at Lopevi's
beach.
>> How exciting.
>> PROBST: When you guys get
back to camp, you'll figure
out a tribe name and paint up
a tribe flag.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Okay, shall we get to
today's challenge?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: This is what you
covet now, individual immunity
from here on out.
Here's the challenge.
It is a water race.
You'll start on the beach, swim
out to a water tower, climb up
the ladder, walk over a balance
beam, grab a flag, jump off and
swim back to shore and put it in
the flag holder.
The first two tribe members to
get all three flags back in
their flag holder move on to the
final round.
Because there are ten of you
we will run two heats, five
each, two people from the first
heat, two people from the second
heat will move into the final.
One person will win immunity.
The other nine, vulnerable at
the next Tribal Council.
Clear?
>> Clear.
>> PROBST: All right.
We'll draw numbers to figure out
your position.
Let's go.
Here we go.
The first heat is Julie, Eliza,
Leann, Chris and Sarge.
The first two to finish move on
to the final round.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Sarge first to the ladder.
Chris right behind, then
Leann, Eliza and Julie.
Sarge is in the water, Eliza
in the water.
Chris in the water.
Julie and Leann bringing up the
rear.
Sarge back with one.
Eliza right behind.
Chris right behind.
Julie and Leann struggling.
Sarge back on the beam.
He's got his second flag.
Eliza, she has her second flag.
Chris making up some time.
Leann wearing down.
Sarge back with two flags, going
for his third.
Chris catching on Eliza and
passing her.
Julie back with her second.
Sarge first in the water with
his third and final flag.
Remember, first two to finish
make it to the final round.
Going to be between Eliza and
Chris for the third flag.
Sarge moving on to the final
round.
Eliza has taken Chris over
again.
She's in the lead.
It's going to be a race for
second place between Eliza and
Chris.
Who will get back first?
>> Kick, it Chris, kick it.
>> PROBST: Sarge and Eliza
moving on to the final round.
>> Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Okay.
The second heat of five.
Rory, Chad, Twila, Scout
and Ami.
First two to finish move on to
the final.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Rory first to the tower.
Ami heading up the tower.
Twila and Chad right behind.
Rory first up, Ami right behind.
Twila still in it.
Rory first one back with his
first flag.
Ami right behind.
Chad right behind.
>> Hustle, Chad.
>> PROBST: Twila bringing up
the rear and Scout giving a
great effort.
Rory has a big lead.
Chad hanging on.
He's not fallen off yet.
Fighting to stay in this.
Scout back with one.
Rory with his second flag.
Ami with her second flag.
Can Chad make up enough time?
Rory and Ami, both winded.
Looking to get into that last
round.
Rory and Ami are neck and neck.
Rory wants to win this thing.
Rory, Ami, moving on to the
final round.
All right, here we go.
Final round.
Rory, Sarge, Ami, Eliza.
First person back with all three
flags wins immunity.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Sarge out to a fast lead.
Ami trying to stay close.
Eliza right behind.
Sarge up the ladder.
Rory up the ladder.
Sarge has his first flag.
Rory in the water.
Ami places her jump.
Eliza in the water.
Rory's going to have to hustle
if he wants a shot at immunity.
Sarge back with one.
Anything could happen.
Rory back with one.
Ami back with one.
Eliza back with one.
>> Come on, Sarge!
>> PROBST: Sarge has his second
flag, Rory right behind.
Keep moving, Rory.
Let's go, Ami.
Sarge wants that immunity.
He's back with his second flag.
Everybody worn out.
Running this back-to-back,
taking its toll.
Ami pushing.
>> Come on, Ami!
You got one more!
>> PROBST: Sarge in the water
with his third flag.
Rory and Ami falling behind.
Eliza out of it.
Sarge wins first individual
immunity.
>> Good job, Sarge.
>> You did a good job.
>> You animal.
>> PROBST: Sarge, come on up
here.
See if this will fit over that
big noggin.
Congratulations.
Safe at the next vote.
Everybody else on this new tribe
vulnerable.
You'll head back to the former
Lopevi beach, figure out a new
tribe name and figure out who
is going home at the next Tribal
Council.
Good effort.
Head on back.
( whooping )
>> Lopevi and Yasur were
merged today.
We picked the Lopevi camp, kind
of mutually, and for the first
time since day one I'm putting
the game behind me, and I'm
going to just have some fun with
these people that I've never
met.
( talking and laughing )
>> I am thrilled.
I just missed Twila deep down in
places I can't talk about.
It's just a happy moment, you
know.
Coming together, reunions
are always a happy moment.
>> Oh, my God!
( talking excitedly )
Food!
>> We come back to Lopevi
beach, and there was a big
celebration feast waiting for
us.
( talking excitedly )
We had cheese and crackers and
dried fruit, and they had a
bunch of leftover chocolate
cake.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Wine.
>> That's awesome.
>> I want a nut.
>> Salute.
>> Yeah, salute.
( whooping, laughing )
>> This place is off the
chain right now.
We got wine in the outrigger
here.
We've got two tribes come
together and I mean, everybody
is just so happy.
It's a festival right now, and
I'm enjoying it.
Yeah!
>> Look at Sarge.
>> There's coffee.
>> Sarge, you're going to
take off like a rocket.
>> I will really enjoy the
coffee, believe me.
>> I am just so completely
ecstatic to be back among men.
I mean, I never thought I would
make it out of Yasur.
>> It was different when y'all
left.
Real different when y'all left.
>> Man, I'm so tired of
having female conversation.
Ami is...
>> Yeah.
>> Chad is a total blast
to be around.
It's great listening to him.
We've had a good time.
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
We've only been together, like,
ten minutes and right off the
bat, Rory let me know that Bubba
got caught by Ami trying to
throw a signal back to us, and
he got crushed like a doggone
bug.
>> You know, you just got
to talk to Chad, I guess, and...
and see what's up.
>> I want some coffee.
>> Twila, you got a cup
right here for yourself.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> Yeah, I'm going to the
water hole.
>> Sarge, we're out of water.
>> I'm fine, man.
>> I'm cool.
>> We'll just chill here
with the rest of the wine.
( chuckling )
>>  And it won't be long
till I, till I get on back
home.
>> Nice.
>> As soon as we got over
there, they were like, "Rory
you're gone next."
Ami told us that.
>> She just straight out?
>> Straight off the bat.
>> Oh, my...
>> "We have an all women's
union, and you guys are getting
voted out."
>> Oh, my God.
>> I get my water back there.
Some people get it up here.
>> Okay.
>> We knew Ami was all on
the female kick.
We knew it.
>> Ami is the top dog over
there, and Ami has had me
squirming.
>> She's calling the shots?
>> Completely.
>> How condescending?
>> Oh, it's completely
condescending.
>> Sarge!
Where's Sarge at?
He done left, didn't he?
>> We're talking about us
being Lopevi five, right?
Our five-- we are family here.
We are so solid.
I'm like, if there's any
fragmentation whatsoever over
there, maybe we could bring the
minority over to our side and
pick off the majority.
>> The minority is me.
>> Okay.
That's all I need to know.
>> I ain't gonna lie to
you, Rory.
I said you weren't a team
player, so, I mean, we had our
disagreements, and-and they're
behind us, you know.
>> That's water under the
bridge.
>> Yeah.
>> To have both Sarge and
Chad say, "Our original alliance
is still running.
Are you still in?"-- I'm just
the cat who swallowed the
canary right now.
>> The guys, they assure me that
Julie and Twila are 100% with
them, but I don't have any
relationship with Julie and
Twila, so really I'm still not
in the best spot, but quite
frankly, I'm not worried about
that today, because my fortunes
have changed.
I'm just so happy right now.
>> Oh, that's going to be good.
>> This is going to be
the best flag ever.
>> Wow.
The new tribe name is Alinta.
It's an Aboriginal word that
means "we are the fire; we are
the people of the fire."
And they kind of liked that
idea, and took off on it.
( excited murmuring )
>> I know you couldn't
stand it.
>> Well, 'cause I can't
stand it on myself.
I'm so excited about this merge.
It just couldn't be better.
I missed the girls who we'd had
on our original Yasur tribe.
Julie especially, 'cause we,
like, got really close in the
first 12 days and then, you
know, being split apart for the
last nine days, I've missed her
a bunch.
>> You guys are some
painting fools.
>> Even though I got this
pact going and everybody says
don't worry, I see Julie laying
next to Ami, and I get real
nervous.
>> That looks so cool.
>> There is that sense that
a male-female fight might happen
at the end.
It might be a scrap out on the
playground between the males and
the females.
And so then anything can happen.
( Lea speaks indistinctly )
>> Well, Sarge, thanks
for cooking.
That's a nice little treat for
our side of the camp.
You look around at the energy
in the camp.
I don't know.
I just have a sense that the
guys are feeling a little...
uh, uneasy.
>> 'Cause he's stronger,
He's stron... he's a lot
physically stronger than Ami.
>> Are you sure you have him?
>> Yes, I do.
The numbers is where it's at,
Twila.
It's just math.
Rory is trying to get in good
with me 'cause he's...
>> That's why Rory needs
to go tonight.
That's why.
He needs to go tonight.
>> We're down by the creek and
Twila and Julie were bringing
up the point of how strong Rory
is at challenges and how he
can just sweep through these
immunities.
>> You have to get over
that whole thing.
>> No, not really.
( chuckles )
Not really.)
>> It kind of appears to
be men versus women.
It would make sense to do that
because the women are up in
numbers, six to four, and we
could easily vote the men off.
>> It's like changing oil
in a damn car.
>> You're not experienced.
>> Ah, well, there's only
one way to get experience.
I really wanted to just start
voting out the guys one by one
and have all women at the end,
because, right now, we're at a
very critical point.
This is a huge turning point of
the game and the first vote is
going to be everything.
>> Chad says that you and Julie
are interested in voting off
Rory.
>> Well, I thought that
was the original game plan.
>> Let me just tell you this.
Rory is guaranteed to give us
numbers.
And listen, Twila.
>> I know.
>> If we vote off Ami,
that breaks the rest of the
girls-- they're done.
>> I just...
>> Twila is just insecure.
She's scared, and you pretty
much have to strategize for
Twila.
We're not making the decision.
We all are making...
>> I'm just trying to get you
all to look at all sides of it.
We can't be playing back and
forth.
>> Maybe you need to talk
to Sarge.
>> It's kind of hard with
ten people around here to talk
to anybody.
>> I know.
>> This is so much fun.
>> Ami has control of all
the women.
She gets them in her aura and
pulls them in and then tells
them what to do, and they run
out like little chickens, you
know, with their head cut off
doing what she says, and she
sits back being the innocent
little girl that doesn't do
anything wrong, and...
and it's dangerous.
It's real dangerous.
Bottom line is I want her away
from Julie, 'cause Julie is
like laying under her arm and
being kissed on the top of the
head by her and stuff, and
telling how hot she is and,
you know, it's just like what
the hell, you know.
I just want her...
>> Out of here.
>> ...out of here before she
infects Julie, and she turns
her charm on you.
>> No.
>> And she says come on,
Twila, let's go lay down.
>> Sarge.
( both laughing )
( speaking indistinctly )
>> No, Twila, lower.
>> Each to their own, but
no thank you.
>> Lower, Twila, there it is.
Right now, with Twila and Julie,
I feel confident about the way
they talk.
They talk with a lot of faith,
a lot of character.
She's a little confused on who
was going home tonight and she
made me a little uneasy for a
second.
But, you know, we have a
pact, and we're sticking
to the pact.
>> All right.
That's all I needed to know.
We can't be playing back
and forth.
>> We're not going to...
>> Because I don't like that.
>> Okay, okay.
>> I just told Chris, I
said, you all make the choice.
If you want to vote for Ami,
just let me know.
Just let me know what you all
want to do, and I'll follow it.
>> I feel confident about Twila.
I feel confident about Julie and
obviously Rory has come back to
Lopevi.
We've got the numbers.
We'll be good to go.
Picking them girls off one by
one is what it's going to be.
>> I got bloody knife on
this one and a spider on this
one.
>> Evil.
>> I don't know, like, what's
been going on throughout
the day, but I don't think that
Twila and Julie ever left the
women's alliance.
They had to do what they had to
do to survive with all men, but
I don't see Twila ever, ever
leaving the women's alliance.
>> Stick five tight, and
we've got it made.
>> Okay.
>> We're going to be in
trouble tonight.
>> We are.
What are we going to do?
>> Play the game.
The guys think we're with them.
The girls automatically think
we're with them, so who knows?
After tonight, somebody is going
to be pissed, but we've got to
do what we've got to do.
I feel bad because I care about
every one of them, but I'm
beating them to the punch.
I'm cutting their throat before
they cut mine.
>> PROBST: Welcome.
First things first.
I got to know what the new
tribe name is. Ami?
>> Alinta.
>> PROBST: Alinta.
Sarge, how'd you come up with
that?
>> The name came from
Scout, who knew the word for
fire-maker, so we figured it's
appropriate, Islands of Fire,
fire-maker.
>> PROBST: Julie, what happened
in terms of workload and
leadership and all that?
>> Well, gosh, half the
tribe worked on the flag and a
lot of people went for wood, and
oh, yeah, a lot of the day was
spent on body paint.
>> PROBST: Who does the best
work?
>> Oh, this one right here.
That one's by far is the best.
>> Yes.
( all laughing )
>> PROBST: Well, don't waste
your flirting on me.
I can't help you any.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: Leann.
Would you have preferred to stay
as the Yasur tribe and let
Lopevi stay as the Lopevi tribe?
>> No. I mean, I think a merge
signifies getting further
in the game.
I mean, having us all come
together feels like, "God, we
really made it this far," and
this is where it should get fun
and interesting and screwy.
>> PROBST: Rory, you've got to
feel like you were just given a
second chance.
>> I know for a fact that I've
been given a second chance,
because Vegas wouldn't have
given me odds on making it out
of the Yasur camp, quite
frankly.
I struggled and I scratched and
I clawed and I prayed and I
hoped that I'd hit a merger for
an opportunity for a shot at
the second half of the game, and
that's what I've been able to
pull through.
>> PROBST: Ami, did you think
you'd make it this far?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Based on what?
What skills do you bring to
this game?
>> What skills do I bring...?
A da... a good attitude.
A good attitude, no matter what.
Even when things are getting
rough, I usually have a good
attitude.
It's gotten me this far in
life, so...
Play with a smile and good
attitude.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
tonight's vote.
It's always tough when you get
to the merge, because you never
know what's going to happen.
You don't know who you can trust
and who you can't trust.
Twila, do you feel a little
stuck in the middle because
you've been on both tribes?
>> Most definitely.
Oh, most definitely.
I feel real stuck in the middle.
I've enjoyed both tribes.
I felt more at ease around the
guys-- there's no doubt about
that.
But, you know, you form
alliances with one side and then
another side and you're kind of
stuck in the middle, but
tonight, no matter which way it
goes, it's gonna be tough.
>> PROBST: Sarge, you have the
immunity necklace, if you want
to assign it to somebody else,
you can.
>> Nope. It's mine tonight.
>> PROBST: All right.
Sarge is the only person you
can't vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
With that, it's time to vote.
Chris, you're up.
>> You're just the, um,
unfortunate victim of the
master plan.
>> RORY: Ami, this is the first
time that I've made a completely
personal vote.
Your treatment of me over the
last nine days has been
horrible.
I have little or no respect for
you, and I really hope that,
like a bad rash, you're
finally gone.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Ami.
That's two votes Ami.
Ami. Three votes Ami.
Ami.
That's four votes Ami.
Rory.
Four votes Ami, one vote Rory.
Two votes Rory, four votes Ami.
Rory.
That's four votes Ami, three
votes Rory.
We're tied.
Four votes Rory, four votes Ami.
Rory. That's five votes Rory,
four votes Ami.
Ninth person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu, Rory.
Bring me your torch.
Rory, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, you are the final nine.
Seven of you will make up the
jury, two will make it to the
final Tribal Council.
One will win a million dollars.
Grab your torches, head back
to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> Camp sucks, kissing and
I want to cuddle with you.
I'm tired of hearing "I love
you, you love me."
>> I'm pro love, man.
>> It makes me sick.
>> PROBST: And Alinta gets a new
pet.
>> Help! Come here!
>> It's a pig.
>> I can taste his fatback
cooked up with my cabbage.
>> No, no, you can't eat him.
>> I think that I am the victim
of a gender war right now.
The women, they have got the men
bamboozled into thinking that
they had an opportunity.
I may not be a million dollars
richer, but I will never forget
the Islands of Fire.
No one has enjoyed the
experience of being on this land
more than I have.