>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor:
>> ( laughs ): We shocked
the shiznit out of them.
>> PROBST: The men swallowed
their pride after they were
deceived, when the women's
alliance rejoined forces and
voted off Rory.
>> It's gonna be tough to
survive the rest of this game.
>> No way!
>> PROBST: And the tribe got a
new pet.
>> Chris!
Oh, my God!
>> Here, pig, pig, pig, pig...
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't eat him.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
Eliza out of the game.
>> Shows you just where
you are, doesn't it, boys?
>> PROBST: Politics and trivia
helped Leann come out on top.
Leann wins reward.
>> I won something!
>> PROBST: She chose Julie to
join her.
>> Can you believe we
said that?
( laughter )
Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: The girls then shared
a picnic on the rim of a dormant
volcano.
>> Hello.
>> Oh, wow.
>> PROBST: The two talked
strategy, and Julie made her
move.
>> I'd be down.
I'd be faithful.
>> Yes?
>> I would.
Cheers.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Back at camp...
>> Look at you.
She's all pissed off.
>> PROBST: Eliza was livid,
because the challenge revealed
the girls' pecking order, and
she was first to go.
>> It is personal.
It's definitely personal.
>> Oh, Eliza, good grief!
>> PROBST: The men saw an
opportunity to break the women's
alliance.
>> We see a weakness
right there.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Ami mastered the
puzzle...
Ami wins immunity.
...and claimed victory.
Safe tonight at the vote is this
woman, Ami.
Back at Alinta...
>> You're a horrible dancer.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: ...Scout worried that
Julie had charmed Leann and
stole her "final four" spot.
>> Jules and Leann have
gotten to be kind of tight since
they went on their little trip
together.
Hell, I might get sent home
tonight.
>> PROBST: And Chris considered
his own strategies.
>> We don't have the
numbers.
Unless we can pull something off
with Twila and Eliza, it's over.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, the women's alliance
held strong, and Chris made a
move to save himself.
>> This is for you, not
against you.
>> PROBST: Tenth person voted
out of Survivor: Vanuatu...
Sarge, the tribe has spoken.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
( snorting )
>> That was the toughest
Tribal Council I've been to.
>> Me, too.
>> And I can tell everybody why.
>> Why?
>> Ten minutes before we
left camp, Sarge asked me who I
was voting for.
I told him I hadn't decided, and
I didn't know, that I-I just
didn't know what to do.
Right before we started walking,
he grabbed me by the shoulder
and told me to vote for him.
I asked him why.
He said, just do it, everybody
else is.
I voted for Sarge.
I told them that Sarge told me
to vote for him, but he didn't.
Um, I voted for Sarge...
to stay close to the women and,
you know, go further in the
game.
You know, this is for the best.
Uh, this is for my personal, you
know, reasons in the game to try
to get as far as I can.
( birds singing )
>> ( whispering ): Ami and
Leann have turned.
They've changed their alliance
from, uh, Twila and myself being
in the top four, moving Jules
into a spot, and she didn't
deserve it.
I'm not gonna sit by and let
that happen.
This morning I went to the guys
at the fire, and I whispered to
them that I had plan to keep
them in the game.
I asked them not to tell
anybody.
Told them I needed to talk to
Twila, and I'd get back with
them.
The plan that I have would take
out Eliza, then take out Ami.
We got to get Ami out of there.
She's a strong contender, and
she's, uh, manipulative, and
it's a whole different game,
then.
>> We have mail.
Wild mail.
"To this challenge, you'll bring
your pig.
Some will push and some will
dig.
It just depends on how you move
through the earth.
Today you'll see how much your
little piggy's worth."
>> Oh...
( snorting )
>> Want me to carry him?
>> Yeah.
>> This ought to be real
fun with this pig today.
( pig squealing )
( indistinct chatter )
>> PROBST: The Alinta mascot.
>> He needs a buff.
>> PROBST: You know, I thought
you might want a buff.
I did have one ready.
Chris, you want to do the
honors?
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: Does he have a name?
>> He's had about 15
names, but Piggy is what stuck.
Piggy.
>> PROBST: Come on, buddy.
>> Here you go.
Go on.
>> PROBST: Has it been nice
having a little company at camp?
>> Not when you're
hungry, and you want meat.
( laughter )
>> Twila.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Sure thing.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge,
you will be randomly divided
into two tribes of four.
You'll compete in this obstacle
course.
One person will be your
sacrificial lamb.
They will be attached to a rope
which runs the entire length of
this obstacle course.
They will also have their hands
tied.
So the other three tribe members
will be responsible for getting
them through all five stages of
the course.
For the first stage, you'll go
up and over a three-level fence.
You'll then maneuver through a
series of hitching posts.
You'll then climb up and over a
wall.
You will then dig under a log.
And then finally, you will
maneuver through a vertical rope
maze.
First tribe to get all four of
their people to their final
tam-tam wins reward.
You want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The winning foursome
will leave here, be taken to
another island for an overnight
visit...
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: ...where you will be
hosted by a village.
This will be an amazing,
once-in-a-lifetime experience
with a tribe who lives very
differently from you.
You'll be treated to all kinds
of cultural activities,
including a major feast.
>> Oh, wow!
>> Oh!
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: Because it is
customary to bring a token of
appreciation...
>> The pig.
>> PROBST: ...
you will bring the
pig, and give this to the
village.
All right, for the two groups,
we're gonna draw numbers.
Let's go down and get started.
All right, here are the teams on
the black rope: Scout, Twila,
Julie and Leann.
Julie is the sacrificial lamb.
On the orange rope: Chad, Ami
Eliza and Chris.
Eliza is the sacrificial lamb.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors, ready...
go!
>> You need help?
You need a push?
>> PROBST: Julie up and over.
>> Come on.
>> Now what?
>> PROBST: Chris grabs Eliza who
somersaults.
>> Get her, get her, get her.
>> I got her, I got her.
I got you, Eliza.
>> Hurry, girl.
Hurry, girl.
>> PROBST: Julie moving.
>> Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Oh, yeah... nope.
>> Got you.
>> PROBST: Up and over again...
>> Over, Chad.
>> PROBST: ...at the mercy of
her team.
>> Oh, she's stuck.
>> Slack is...
>> Chad, pull her through.
Chad, pull her through.
>> PROBST: Eliza up and over one
more time, and we're just on the
first part of the course.
>> Get her, Chad, get her.
>> Nice and easy.
>> You all right?
Go, go...
>> PROBST: Eliza through the
first obstacle, races ahead to
the hitching post.
>> Give me slack.
>> PROBST: Julie, Twila, Leann
and Scout falling behind.
>> Here, here.
>> PROBST: Julie being held in
mid-air.
>> Bring you down...
>> Thanks, Chris.
Wait.
Her legs are caught.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Eliza stuck in the
rope...
>> Chad, get over there
and give me some slack.
>> PROBST: ...trying to get her
legs undone.
>> Don't pull your legs.
>> Oh, oh, real good.
Take your time.
>> Yeah...
>> PROBST: Chad just yanks them
out.
>> I got her.
>> Up and around and down
and out.
Go, go, go...
>> PROBST: Julie's through the
first obstacle.
>> Go, go, go!
Out of the way.
Go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go...
>> PROBST: Julie's tribe arrives
at the second obstacle.
>> Go.
>> You got her?
You sure?
>> PROBST: Eliza getting tossed
again.
>> Just hurry, up and over.
>> PROBST: Up and over.
That belly is going to have some
marks.
>> Good job, Eliza.
>> Okay...
>> Slacks on the other
way, the other way.
>> Slack.
Slack, slack,
slack, slack...
>> PROBST: Eliza's tribe doing a
great job with the slack,
working her way around the post.
>> Lots of slack.
>> PROBST: They're through the
hitching post.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Eliza, Chad, Chris
and Ami on to the third
obstacle.
>> Nice job.
>> Let's go, girl.
Let's go, girl.
Here you go...
>> One more.
( Julie grunts )
>> You all right?
You all right?
>> Some more.
>> Some more...
>> ...slack.
I'll get the slack.
You get her?
Get her.
>> PROBST: Eliza, up and over
the wall.
Great teamwork.
>> Put me down, put me
down.
>> Okay, now go, go, go,
go, go.
>> PROBST: Here comes Julie,
Twila, Scout and Leann.
They've made up some time.
>> Go, go.
All right...
>> PROBST: They really move to
stay in this.
>> Under and over.
Under and over.
Now, one more time around and
back.
>> PROBST: Julie really throwing
herself over these walls.
Eliza, Chris, Chad and Ami still
with the lead.
>> Step, step.
>> PROBST: Julie, Twila, Leann
and Scout are working hard to
catch up.
>> Come on, come on.
>> PROBST: Julie launches
herself over again.
>> Pull it.
>> The stomach rolls.
>> Come on.
I got you.
Come on.
Down this way.
>> Got you.
>> Drop your feet, drop
your feet.
>> PROBST: Ami leading Eliza
through, and she's out.
>> Come on, come on.
>> Jump up, Jules.
Jump up, Jules.
>> All right, run, run.
>> Hurry, hurry, they're
right on us, they're right on
us.
>> Come on.
>> Through, through.
>> I don't know if this
is gonna work.
>> PROBST: They've dug a hole.
Will she fit?
>> Fit, fit, fit...
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Going to take her
face off.
>> Pull, pull.
>> PROBST: Chris pulls her
through anyway.
>> Come on, guys.
Come on...
>> PROBST: Julie, shoving
herself through.
>> Ow!
>> PROBST: Leann yanks on her.
>> Come on.
Go.
Come on, got you.
>> My shoulders, my shoulders.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Eliza going through
for her second time.
Once again, just misses her
nose.
They're on to the final
obstacle.
Chad, Chris, Eliza and Ami at
the final vertical rope maze.
>> Okay, now, go.
Now got down.
Yeah, that's right.
>> Come on, come on...
>> Pull, pull...
>> PROBST: Julie going to have
to go face first in the sand.
Why they're going this way, I
don't know, but they're through.
This is it.
Both tribes at the final
vertical rope maze.
Eliza starting to make her way
through the rope maze.
>> Those guys are coming.
Quick.
>> Nice job.
>> PROBST: Julie enters the rope
maze, shoving the rope over.
Very close.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Step up...
>> Take a step.
Step.
>> Come on.
They're trying again.
Come on, come on.
>> ...Too slow.
Bring that low.
There you go.
Step through.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Eliza's team still
with the lead.
>> Yup.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Julie trying to catch
up.
Chris just going to shove her
through.
Chris and Chad carrying Eliza
through this rope maze.
Twila, Scout, Julie and Leann
are making up ground.
Julie having to pull herself up.
Ami and Twila trying to help
out.
>> Want me to lift...?
>> Nice job.
>> PROBST: Chad, Eliza, Ami,
very
close.
>> One more.
>> PROBST: Twila, Leann, Scout
and Julie not giving up, though.
>> This...this one right here.
>> ...through.
Come on.
>> She doesn't need it.
>> PROBST: Chris just shoves
Eliza through, using his
strength.
>> A leg.
>> You are through.
You are through!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: That's it.
Eliza, Chad, Ami, Chris win
reward.
( cheering )
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: ...overnight visit.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Julie, you were
getting tossed around, banged
around-- how you doing?
>> I'm fine.
>> PROBST: Are you upset because
you lost or because you're hurt?
>> Uh, 'cause we lost.
It's a lot of work.
>> PROBST: You guys, get your
stuff, head back to camp.
For you four, you will have a
great experience, a chance to
get away from camp, fill up
your bellies.
Take your pig, head on out and
have a good night.
>> Ami, Chad, Chris and
I, we're going on an overnight
visit in a village, and we were
so excited, and we were bringing
Piggy as a gift for the tribe
that we are visiting.
But Piggy peed on the plane.
That stunk.
>> Wonderful flight,
Captain.
( pig squealing )
>> How long you going to
be a grouch?
>> We were in the very,
very back country.
I don't think we could have
gone any further to get away
from civilization.
>> It seemed like we
went to a whole other world.
>> Who should we give the
pig to?
( indistinct talking )
>> Chief.
None of us knew what to expect.
People from the village looking
at us, and we're looking at
them, and I'm carrying a pig.
Chief.
We'd like to offer you this.
( pig squealing )
>> We handed the chief
Piggy, and he was very
appreciative, and they gave us
a pig back.
>> Thank you.
( applause )
Me, Ami, Eliza and Chad were
just, like, "Damn, they're
giving us a pig back."
You know, but, yeah...
The pig -- they give us a pig
in return, and they actually
just had us lay it down by a
bench where we were sitting,
and we just never asked for the
pig back.
We didn't want the pig.
( pig snorting )
( tribal singing, chanting )
>> Once they started
dancing, like really doing the
traditional dancing, we were
watching that, it was amazing.
They don't use any instruments.
They just use claps of their
hands, stomp of their feet and
their voices.
Like...
( ululating )
I could feel the vibration of
their feet stomping.
( singing )
It was amazing, like out of a
book.
It looked like we were in the
middle of a book.
( singing )
The chief said "Do you want to
dance?"
And I was like, "Yeah, I want
to dance.
Dancing sounds great."
>> Yes, okay. Okay.
That's wonderful.
Thank you.
They brought us bowls of kava...
and me and Chad and Ami and
Eliza-- we all drank a bowl of
kava.
>> Drink.
>> You drink the whole thing?
>> Yeah, yeah, the whole thing,
yeah.
>> Oh.
>> You just say...
Okay, you chug it, and then you
spit out your last sip.
And this bowl was enormous, and
it kind of tastes like mud mixed
with water and vodka.
( spitting )
Almost immediately, my mouth
started feeling numb, and my
tongue started feeling numb.
It was definitely a strange
feeling.
( spitting )
>> The kava is powerful,
very, very powerful.
>> Like, I feel sort of
buzzed, but my inclination is
just, "Whoa, wait."
>> Yeah.
You're holding on to my
shoulders for dear life.
>> After that kava, I
started spinning into a kava-
induced, uh...stupor.
>> Chad had too much kava.
>> I'm all right.
>> You wild man.
>> God, I can barely stand up.
I am thrown from that kava.
I couldn't walk.
I couldn't...
I wasn't coordinated.
>> The kava tore him up!
The kava tore him up!
We'll never experience nothing
like this again the rest of our
lives.
>> Uh-uh.
Wow, man...
wow.
>> Smells delicious.
That looks good.
( laughing )
>> When we were thinking
feast, we were thinking plates
of steak, anything cooked...
but they had the cow's head and
then banana leaves laid out, and
they had all this meat just
piled on it.
What's it like?
>> Uh...
rubber.
It wasn't cooked all the way.
There wasn't a lot of flavor to
it.
There was a lot of... fat.
It just wasn't something that I
was used to.
The food definitely isn't the
reward part of this.
>> No.
( singing in native language )
All the children were gathered
around this little tiny fire,
and they were teaching the song
that they had learned for the
Americans, and their smiles
touched me in a way I'll never
forget.
This was the highlight of my
entire night.
( singing )
>> ♪ We are very happy
When you visit
Our...
village here today. ♪
>> It was the most
unbelievable reward we could've
possibly ever gotten.
( cheering )
Yeah!
>> I'm catching on to that song.
>> Yeah.
( thunder crashing )
( Scout groaning )
>> I think that'll help
the fire for a little while.
Oh, God.
>> It's been raining forever!
>> Oh, man, it is just
raining cats and dogs.
It looks like it's set in for
days.
Everything is soaking wet.
It's going to be a miracle if we
can keep our fire.
I-I've never been in a worse
situation than this, really.
>> This is the...
by far
the worst night, by far the
worst night.
It won't stop ...
raining, and I
don't care if I can't swear.
( laughing )
It won't stop raining.
It's freezing.
Everything we have is soaked.
I don't even want to think about
what the other four are doing at
the moment.
I'm sure they're having a great
time, and they're comfortable,
and that's just enough to make
me mad thinking about it.
>> Piss and moan!
( laughing )
That's all we can do!
>> God, oh, and wait for it to
go away.
>> I had one hell of a night.
It rained cats and dogs, and our
shelter just...
it just poured in.
Our blankets were drenched.
Our clothes were drenched.
Our pillows are drenched,
everything.
And the timing was just right,
and I said, "You know what,
you guys, keeping this fire
going... I tell you what.
We ought to, uh, send Eliza on
home and, uh, and, uh, keep
these guys around another few
days.
Let 'em help us with the fire
and collecting wood."
Then...
the game changes.
>> ♪ Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! ♪
>> Yeah, you know, her
time's definitely overdue.
>> Thank you.
>> Five on that.
>> She should've...
You all...
I don't know how you
all kept her as long as you did.
I don't know.
>> Yeah, I don't...
>> So, you want to tell Ami?
>> Oh, we can tell Ami. No.
>> I think so.
>> I think Ami's cool
with it, but...
Yeah, the guys don't need to
know.
>> Listen, here's their...
The guys will vote with us,
because here's their choice.
>> "Don't vote with us,
and one of you guys are going
home tonight."
>> "Eliza, or one of you.
Take your pick."
>> That's true.
>> Want to hit the trail
mix first?
>> Yes.
>> There's no fire.
I'll start on it.
Is that cool?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> You guys want to
coconut it up?
>> We'll coconut...
>> Hey.
Home sweet home.
>> Did it rain on you guys?
>> Oh, yeah, it rained
off and on.
>> But-but you were inside.
>> Um, we ended up in a
hut at the end of the night that
didn't ra...
that didn't, um... leak.
>> But the food and the
sleeping arrangements,
seriously, were horrible.
>> Swear to God.
>> But you didn't have to
sleep with wet blankets, and you
didn't get poured on, right?
>> We did not get poured
>> At least there's that.
>> When-when we got back,
it was as if...
they couldn't be
less excited to see us.
>> It was nice to be around
the kids.
That my favorite, favorite,
favorite, favorite part.
And all I could see was the sea
of little kids' faces all around
the fire-- this little tiny
fire.
We were all hunched down.
I was sitting down on the ground
like this.
They were all hunched all
around, and I could feel a
little kid's head on my head.
I loved that part.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Very interesting.
Coming back to camp, there was
no welcome.
Just could care a less.
"Whatever, you had a good time,
whatever, yadda, yad.
Sit down and do your work or
whatever you need to do."
It's pretty much how the welcome
went.
But I could definitely tell
something had gone on.
I had really weird feelings.
Jules didn't...
wouldn't look me
in the face, would not look me
in the face, which makes me
think, "Oh, God, what
conversations have been going on
while I haven't been here?"
>> You want to hear about
the whole plan?
>> Yes, I'd love to.
>> You want to hear the
whole plan?
All right, Jules, Leann, Twila,
myself-- we all want to get rid
of Liza.
Like having a rattlesnake in
your pocket.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> So, we got to keep
Liza from getting immunity,
anybody get immunity but Liza,
and vote Liza off, and then from
there, we got to get rid of Ami
immediately.
We've got to get Ami out,
because she is...
>> The brains.
>> And we'll play ball
with you guys, 'cause we think
it will be a lot more fun.
>> It would.
It will be.
>> We just really love
you guys.
I'm just thrilled.
>> I'm not going to make
this obvious,
I'm going to head back with
my wood.
Yeah, things have changed.
There's dissension in the ranks.
The women are not tight, and the
women come across cocky,
confident.
They have since the merge,
since Rory went home, and it
got to Scout the way the other
girls were coming across-- you
know, the cocky way Ami presents
herself.
Me and Chad, we're doing our
best.
We're playing it.
We're tugging at their hearts.
They are rolling in it.
Scout bit.
You question a woman's
character, you question a
woman's ability, she'll snap
your neck.
You open up your heart, show a
woman you're vulnerable, then
they start thinking with their
heart.
That's when they open up that
back door.
That's what's happened this
time.
>> PROBST: Morning.
>> Morning, Jeff.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Sure thing.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Ami, give it up.
Immunity-- back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to climb up a ladder that
is leaning against a post.
On my go, you'll step off of the
ladder, reach out, grab onto the
post and hang on for as long as
you can.
When your feet touch the ground,
you're out of the challenge.
Last person left hanging on the
post wins immunity, safe from
the vote.
We've randomly drawn for your
positions.
Take your spot, wait for my go.
For immunity.
Three, two, one, everybody step
up.
And we are on.
Ami loses a little bit of a
grip.
Twila starting to slide, trying
to find a new footing.
She's got it.
Julie's sliding.
Julie coming down another notch,
finds a bit of rope to put her
feet on.
Twila just bear-hugging it,
trying to find a way to grip it.
Julie first one out.
Have a seat on the pole.
Ami starting to slip.
Holding on with her fingertips.
Chris starting to slide.
Chris is out.
Scout starting to slide.
Scout is out.
Scout joins Chris and Julie.
Ami sliding down.
That can't feel good.
Ami's out.
Take a spot on the pole.
Eliza starting to slide.
>> Oh, God!
>> PROBST: Ooh!
You all right?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: We are down to three.
Immunity at stake.
Tribal council tonight.
Twila biting the rope, going to
hold on with her teeth.
Chad starting to show signs of
slipping.
>> You're doing good,
Chad.
>> PROBST: Chad struggling to
hang
on, gripping with his thighs.
Twila still chewing on that
rope.
Leann slides, finds a new
foothold.
Twila trying to climb back up.
Every time you move, you risk
falling more.
Chad sliding down a little more.
Leann is struggling.
She's sliding, she's fighting
it.
Leann's out.
We are down to two-- Chad,
Twila.
Chad gripping with his fingers
on that rope.
And Chad is slipping.
>> Go Chad, go down,
Chad.
>> PROBST: Chad's slipping,
looking for something to get a
foot on.
The last bit of rope.
>> Go down, Chad, go.
Go down, Chad.
Go down, Chad, go down, Chad.
Please, God, go down, Chad.
>> PROBST: Chad is out.
Twila wins immunity.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Nice work.
All right, Twila, turn around
here.
I know you want this.
>> Yes.
JEFF: Feels good?
>> PROBST: Safe from the vote
tonight.
Everybody else on the block.
You'll vote somebody out and
have another member of our jury.
I'll see you there.
Get your stuff and head back to
camp.
>> Thanks, man.
>> So, are we voting for
Chad tonight?
>> I think there's a way
that, you know, if we were to
give the guys longer in the
game, I think there's a way we
could go ahead and send Liza
home.
You just have to spend one night
sitting in a downpouring rain
trying to keep a fire going to
appreciate...
>> I sat out here by myself
one night and kept the fire
going all night.
I'm willing to do fire duty with
you.
It just scares me to think that
one of the girls would be going
home before the guys.
>> You and Jules and
Leann, you're such strong
competitors.
>> I think we got most of
the big rocks.
Scout and I were definitely at
odds about how the vote should
go.
She really wants to get rid of
Eliza, but I thought getting rid
of Eliza tonight was not a good
idea at all.
Let's kind of stick to the game
plan, and not have to worry
later that there's two strong
men that could win immunity, and
we're going to have to start
voting out women.
One of these guys can make it
all the way to the end.
This game is not over.
So are we for sure voting Chad
tonight?
>> I'm still up in the
air right now.
>> I think that's a good idea.
Don't you think?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know.
>> It was just making me
excited the other way.
>> I know.
>> Everyone excited.
>> Going to Tribal Council
for me is just let's get it
done.
Let's take care of the vote,
let's get home, let's work on
tonight and hopefully start out
with a nice, dry day tomorrow.
I don't think it's time for
Eliza to be voted off yet.
I just don't.
>> After getting back from
the challenge, everybody's mood
seemed to be a little different.
I just sensed that Scout was not
getting the results from the
other women to vote for Eliza.
Gotta hydrate; big night around
the fire tonight.
At this point, I'm just going to
try to reassure those in ourg to
voting bloc, which is what I
think is our voting bloc, to
keep with the same vote that we
had planned.
So, it's still the same vote
tonight, right?
Has everything changed?
>> I have no idea what's
going on.
>> Are you kidding me?
>> No, ma'am, sir.
I thought you said they talked
to you.
>> Who, Chris?
>> No, uh... Scout.
>> Well, she's been saying
stuff for, you know, the last
few days, and everything looks
good, but just from what Ami
and, uh, just from what, the way
that they're acting, man, it
just doesn't look good for me.
>> Here you go.
I want to get out of the rain.
I'm about half dry.
>> Man, it is up in the
air right now, and there's some
last-minute fierce negotiation.
Twila has immunity tonight, so
there's no reason she shouldn't
vote with us.
>> Honey, don't ask me.
I'm not the person to ask.
I'm certainly not the person to
ask.
>> There's only one person
that's made...
>> So I'm pissed.
>> Are you?
Well, we are, too.
>> You friggin' pissed me off.
>> Really?
>> Well, I've been wanting to
get rid of her since day one.
>> We have an...
>> But it don't matter to me.
I told... I told Ami, "Whatever
you all decide, come back and
let me know," 'cause it don't
matter to me.
I just don't like the bitch.
>> I know.
>> I didn't like her from day,
and I want to get rid of her.
>> I know.
>> But...
>> Yeah.
>> It's drama central today.
( Leann laughs )
It is friggin' soap opera-ville.
>> Yep.
>> Scout?
>> Yeah?
>> You know you got Ami
asking all kinds of questions.
She don't want to vote for
Eliza.
She wants to go ahead and vote
one of the guys out.
She thinks it's stupid to vote
for one of the women when you
still got two guys that can win
immunity, and she's right.
I don't know.
I feel like I'm being pulled
from both directions.
I'm being pulled, because you
feel like you're fifth, so you
want me to go with you, and I'm
feeling like they're...
I don't know if I can trust them
or not, and I'm going, "You
know, I don't know what to do
here," but they're not going to
vote for Eliza.
I'm telling you right now, them
four...
It's going to be four against
four.
>> All right, will you...
will you let me talk and listen
to the logic?
>> You gonna have to hurry,
'cause I got to go that a'way.
>> The logic is, is that
we have, with the two guys and
you and me, we have four votes
to their three votes.
>> But that's not going
to happen, though.
They're not going to do it, and
somebody's going to have to draw
a rock tonight and go home.
Would you like to be out of this
game by a friggin' stone?
Well, I wouldn't.
>> All right, so... so what
what you're going to...
>> I'm not going to do
nothing yet.
I'm still thinking.
I'm aggravated, but I have to go
this way.
I definitely feel stuck in the
middle right now, and it's
tearing me up, 'cause I don't
know.
You know, it's like I'm going to
get somebody pissed off at me
either way, so I'm screwed.
The guys are depending on me and
Scout to pull through for them.
That's the only way they're
going to stay in the game.
I don't know which way to go.
You know, I'd really...
Yes, I'm like Scout.
Yes, I'd like the hands to be
turned and Ami not be in charge
right now, but I don't know if
that's going to happen.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the first member of our jury,
Sarge, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
He is here merely to observe and
gather information.
Big change in the weather last
few days.
A lot more water.
Rain coming down.
Everybody here seems to be cold.
Leann, does that change anything
at this point in the game?
>> Um, I'm not good with
the rain.
I'm worried that I'm just going
to... freak out and not be able
to handle it.
It makes me crazy!
>> PROBST: Chris, no secret
there's been talk of the women
sticking together and picking
off the men.
Have you noticed in the last
couple of days that maybe your
stock and Chad's stock might've
gone up a little bit?
>> Absolutely.
It's crossed my mind that, you
know, possibly, our stock, you
know, did go up because of what
we can do around camp.
>> PROBST: Chad, guys have taken
some knocks.
You still fighting in this game?
>> Hell, yeah, we're still
fighting.
I-I'll tell you.
Chris and I have come up with
about 25 or 30 different plans,
different ways of weaseling out
of-of this situation we're in.
>> PROBST: Scout, are you seeing
scurrying around, or has anybody
come up to you?
>> Yes, many people have
come up, and, uh, we've talked
quite a bit about different
strategies and plans to get to
the end of the game.
>> PROBST: Scout-- and you guys
tell me if I'm wrong-- do you
think Chris and Chad are both
listening, thinking, "Maybe our
plans have worked?"
>> I think the guys have
talked to everybody.
>> Not me.
>> It's not just me.
>> And not me.
>> PROBST: So this is news to
you?
>> Yeah, and it makes me
nervous that-that two women
might be voting with the two
men, and that it will be a
four-four tie, and that's
exactly what makes me
uncomfortable.
>> PROBST: Do you think you
might've have missed out on
something being gone?
>> Definitely possible, yeah.
I mean, it's possible that that
night brought them together in
such a way that things have
changed since then.
>> PROBST: Well, here was my
question.
Twila, do you think you'll ever
get used to the fact that you
can never ever feel safe?
>> When it comes right
down to it, you can't trust
anybody.
The most'll be 99.
9%, but...
I don't know.
Y-You always have that little
bit in your mind, "Can I, or can
I not?"
>> PROBST: Now, Ami, you have a
smile on your face that's so
smug.
>> Yeah, 'cause I think
that is such bull...
I don't question that one bit.
Like, I definitely know that
there are people I can trust,
and I know I can be trusted.
>> PROBST: And we'll find out if
you're sitting in the final two
whether you're right or whether
you're wrong.
>> Totally, totally.
>> PROBST: All right.
Okay, it is time to vote.
Twila, you have immunity.
I'm guessing you're not giving
that up.
>> No.
>> PROBST: All right, Twila is
the only person you cannot vote
for. Everybody else is fair
game.
It is time to vote.
Scout, you're up.
>> Chad, I'm sorry.
I have to stick true to my
alliance and my word, and you're
the next one to go.
Sorry, bud.
>> Eliza, you've been on
the chopping block seems like
forever, and with this vote, I
hope that my alliance stays
strong.
>> Eliza, I'm voting for
you because your alliance people
told me to vote for you.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out'll be asked to
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Eliza.
Two votes Eliza.
Chad.
Two votes Eliza, one vote
Two votes Eliza, two votes Chad.
Chad.
Three votes Chad, two
votes Eliza.
Chad.
That's four votes Chad,
two votes Eliza.
11th person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu: Chad.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Chad, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, with only one man, the
women in this tribe must now
begin to think, "Hmm, where do I
fall in the pecking order?"
And suddenly, that one man could
become very valuable.
12 days left.
Gonna be fun.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> Scout and Twila come
to me and Chad, wanting to form
an alliance with us.
Swear to God on my family's
lives.
I narced out Scout and Twila.
>> PROBST: The girls confront
Scout.
>> It's not Scout's idea.
That is what I'm trying to tell
you.
( hisses )
My hackles came up.
>> Ami was the one that
single-handedly convinced the
women outside of Scout, Twila,
Chris and I to change their vote
from Eliza to me, and I don't
know how she did it, but she did
it.
She used the woman power thing,
and what can I say?
I-I'm not sore or sour, but,
damn, you know?
I wish I could've gone further.