>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> What a worthless crew.
>> PROBST: Rory reached his
breaking point.
>> I'm ready to get the
hell out of Yasur.
>> PROBST: And Rory got his
wish.
Drop your buffs.
The game took a big turn...
Orange is your new color.
...when the tribes merged before
the immunity challenge.
This is what you covet now:
individual immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Sarge!
>> PROBST: Sarge came out on
top.
Sarge wins first individual
immunity.
The new tribe returned to a huge
feast at Lopevi's camp.
>> This place is off the
chain right now.
>> PROBST: And named themselves
Alinta.
>> I'm so tired of having
female conversation.
>> PROBST: Rory immediately
rejoined his male alliance.
>> Ami is the top dog over
there.
>> PROBST: He convinced the men
that Ami was the biggest threat
and an all-female alliance was a
dangerous possibility.
>> Ami says, "We have an all-
women's union, and you guys are
getting voted out."
>> PROBST: With Tribal Council
looming, Ami worked her magic on
the girls.
>> I don't think that Twila
and Julie ever left the women's
alliance.
>> Even though I got a pact
going, I get real nervous.
Ami has control of all the
women, and it's dangerous.
>> We're not making the
decision.
We all are making the decision.
>> PROBST: In the end, it came
down to Twila and Julie.
>> I feel confident about
Twila and Julie.
We got the numbers.
We'll be good to go.
>> The guys think we're
with them.
The girls think we're with them.
After tonight, somebody's going
to be pissed.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Julie and Twila betrayed the men
when they voted off Rory.
Rory, the tribe has spoken.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Where do you guys think the
torch is-- just over here?
>> That was fun.
>> I'd like to say I'm real
happy to be here right now.
>> Yeah, you are.
What about me?
>> Tribal Council tonight
was absolute heaven.
The guys went in thinking they
were getting rid of me tonight,
and, oh, we shocked the shiznit
out of 'em.
>> So this is men against
women.
That's the first time I
realized that.
I've never had anyone waver
in my alliance, and tonight was
the first time that the alliance
wasn't true.
Tribal Council was a surprise.
I would I say that I probably
put a little bit too much...
confidence in Julie and Twila.
They've put me, Sarge and Chad
in a precarious situation.
It's going to be tough to
survive the rest of this game.
I trusted Julie.
I trusted Twila.
I did. I trusted 'em both.
>> I thought I could
trust you all, too, but it
didn't seem like it was going
that way.
>> You learn... every day
of life, you learn a little bit
more about people.
>> Yeah.
>> Tonight's Tribal
Council was tough for me,
because even though Sarge gave
me his word, and Chris gave me
his word, and-and Chad gave me
his word, I felt like I still
couldn't trust the guys.
The guys told me that I was
going to be part of the final
four, and they told Julie the
same thing.
>> You got to trust the
people you're with.
>> I feel like I didn't
do anything more to those guys
than what they would've done to
me.
I've got a lot of guilt.
I didn't like it all.
>> Sleep well, guys.
>> I'm going to bed.
You guys, thanks for dinner.
>> I get the outside.
>> Okay.
>> I do, too.
>> This is how naive
Julie and Twila are.
They think they were at the end
of our pecking order?
Where are they being away from
the other girls all this time?
They're at the end of their
pecking order, but the beauty of
it is that the game's not over.
>> Uh-uh.
>> Anything can happen.
>> I'm just real hurt just
the way... because I thought
Twila was sincere. I just...
>> I guess I don't
understand the reasoning.
>> Yeah.
>> It must... it's just...
>> Well, it's just like...
>> It must just be gender.
It must be a woman thing.
>> That is the truest thing
you just said.
A lot of things going through my
mind.
Uh, I got despisal.
I have, uh, remorse.
Uh, these bunch of women--
they're very conniving, and I...
Hats off to 'em, you know.
You got me.
>> ♪ I'm picking
On the bone
♪ Of memories still held
In my mind
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la
Yeah, and one tiny candle
♪ In the dark
And it's driving me crazy... ♪
>> Bottom line, it's
awkward right now.
It's awkward talking to any of
'em.
>> Think it's a reward
challenge today?
>> Yeah, I think it might be.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
today's reward challenge.
I'm going to ask you a series of
questions about Vanuatu culture.
Each time you answer a question
correctly, you get to light one
other tribe member's ceremonial
skull which has been carved out
of a coconut.
Each tribe member only has three
skulls.
When you're out of skulls,
you're out of the game.
Take a seat on the bench.
For the winner, you will leave
the beach directly aboard a
helicopter, where you will take
a flight through the inland
gorge.
This is a ride-- the ride of a
lifetime.
You will land at Mount Maro,
which is a dormant volcano with
a view you have never seen
before and I doubt will ever
see again.
While you're sitting at the top
of Mount Maro, looking at the
beautiful view, you will partake
in a picnic, a little champagne,
blankets, pillows to sit on and
chicken wings.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Big, big bucketful.
Pick up your cube, and let's
start.
First question.
"The word 'Vanuatu' means
A) land of fire, B) land
eternal, C) land of spirits?"
Correct answer is "B) land
eternal."
Eliza has it right, Sarge has it
right.
Scout has it right.
Eliza, make the first move.
>> This is awful.
Sorry.
>> PROBST: Chad takes the first
hit.
>> Great.
>> PROBST: Sarge.
Sarge seems to know right where
he's headed.
Scout takes a hit.
Will Scout seek retaliation?
Payback is tough.
Sarge is going to take his first
hit.
First round down, Chad takes a
hit, Sarge takes a hit and Scout
takes a hit.
Next question: "The archipelago
of Vanuatu consists of how many
islands-- A) 18, B) 83, C) 28?"
The correct answer is "B) 83."
Everybody got it right.
Eliza, you're first up.
Eliza heads over to Chris.
Lights up his first skull.
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: Leann, Sarge takes
his second hit.
>> Wham!
>> PROBST: Chad, Julie takes her
first hit.
Ami.
>> Sorry, Sarge.
>> PROBST: Sarge going to be the
first casualty in this game.
Sarge, you're out of the game,
but you still have one hit left,
so you'll stay in line.
Chris gives Ami a little hello,
and welcome to the game.
>> She didn't have one.
>> Yeah, thanks.
>> PROBST: Julie gives Chad his
second hit.
Twila.
With that, Chad is out of the
game.
Chad, none too pleased with
that.
Not even pretending to be happy.
>> Not pleased.
>> PROBST: Sarge, this is your
last hit.
Julie going to take her second
hit.
>> I didn't even hit you.
>> Oh, hon, it's beyond that.
( laughter)
>> PROBST: Scout, game is
getting personal quickly.
Chris takes his second hit.
Next question: "According to
Vanuatu culture, large, curved
pig tusks are a sign of a
person's A) wisdom, B) courage,
C) fertility or D) wealth?"
Correct answer is "D) wealth."
Eliza got it right, Twila got it
right, Scout got it right.
Eliza. And with that Chris is
out of the game and takes a
seat on the bench.
>> Sorry.
>> No, it's not a woman-man
thing.
>> Oh, no.
>> Estrogen city.
>> They are bitter.
>> Wow!
We got some bitterness going on.
>> PROBST: Twila... now the
women forced to eat each other.
>> Oh, I see how it is.
>> Always been that way.
>> PROBST: Scout... Leann takes
her first hit.
True or false.
"Local sorcerers often
participate in 'magmay,' a soul-
cleansing ritual in which a
small cup of lava is consumed to
exorcise spirits and evil
demons."
True or false?
Well, the correct answer is
"false."
If you drank lava, you would
die.
>> You'd be dead.
>> PROBST: It would burn all of
your internal organs.
Ami got it right, Twila got it
right and Scout got it right.
Ami, first up.
Twila takes her first hit.
Twila.
Eliza takes her second hit.
>> Second one from her.
>> PROBST: Scout.
The women begin to turn on each
other.
>> Eliza, in deference to
your knowledge.
>> PROBST: With that, Eliza is
out of the game.
>> Shows you just where
you are, doesn't it, boys?
Good to see you guys over here.
>> She's a smart one.
>> And you're really not.
>> You are. You're a smart one.
>> PROBST: This friendly game
just suddenly turned.
>> Oh, ugly.
>> PROBST: True or false.
"Vanuatu has the highest
concentration of different
languages per capita of any
country in the world?"
Correct answer is "true."
Over 100 different local tribal
languages spoken here.
Julie got it right, Twila got it
right and Scout got it right.
Julie.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: Doesn't feel too
good, does it, Scout?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Twila.
Eliza, you're still simmering.
>> Yeah, I am.
I'm not going to lie.
>> Simmer, girl, simmer.
>> PROBST: With that, Julie's
last skull.
We are down to four.
Scout heading toward Ami.
Ami takes her second hit.
Leann still has two skulls, Ami
one, Twila two left, and Scout
one.
"The tam-tam is a unique musical
instrument which is an
indigenous version of a A) horn,
B) rattle, C) drum?"
Correct answer is "C) drum."
Leann got it right and Scout got
it right.
>> Scout, you did it to me.
>> No!
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Leann lights up
Scout's last ceremonial skull.
Scout is out of the game, and
you still have one hit left.
Scout gives it to Ami.
Knocks her out of the game.
Leann with two skulls left.
Twila with two skulls left.
"The national currency of
Vanuatu is the vatu, a word
meaning, A) stone, B) pig,
C) coconut?"
Correct answer is "A) stone."
Go make your hit.
All right, here's where we
stand.
Because Leann has two skulls
left and you only have one,
if Leann gets it right, she wins
reward.
>> Pressure.
>> PROBST: "The national dish of
Vanuatu, A) yam-yam, B) lap-lap,
C) pop-pop?"
The correct answer is "B)
lap-lap."
And with that Leann wins reward.
>> I won something.
>> PROBST: Leann, go make your
last hit and put Twila out of
this game.
>> Look at her, she's so
excited.
>> "I never win a thing.
I never win a thing."
>> PROBST: Okay, Leann,
obviously, it's not any fun
going alone, nobody to share the
memory with.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: Pick one person to go
with you.
>> It's Julie.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Julie.
( Julie and Leann laughing )
Okay, Leann, Julie, you're
getting on a chopper, you're
going to Mount Maro, you're
going to take part in a nice
picnic-- champagne, chicken
wings.
It's yours, come get it, and go.
For you guys, it's over.
Get your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Oh, my God.
I'm so grateful.
Thank you so much.
>> So I won the reward
challenge, and I got to take
someone with me, so I took Julie
because Julie was the one person
I was a little unclear about as
far as where she stood and where
her head was at.
>> Oh, my God.
This is really exciting.
Neither of us had ever come
close to doing anything like
this before, and we were trying
to take it all in, and we're
holding hands, just loving it.
>> Oh, my God!
>> The pilot took us
through, like, the gorge and
down in these big sinkholes.
And-and it was just incredible.
When we finally got to our
destination, which was a dormant
volcano...
we were overlooking a really
steep decline.
Just looking around, and all you
can see is untouched, beautiful
environment.
>> We made it.
>> I expected that a volcano
would look like you see in
pictures.
But, no, I understand that we're
kind of sitting on top of a
dormant volcano, and it's just a
little surreal, and it's not
going to sink in for a while.
>> Got the bubbly.
I just want to lick 'em.
( cork popping )
Oh, wow.
( both laughing )
Leann and I, we've always liked
each other but we've never
really talked strategy, so it
was really good that we had
this opportunity to swap
strategies and talk a little bit
about what was going on in the
game.
>> Eliza's comments worry the
...out of me.
>> Mm-hmm. And the guys are...
the guys are so feeding her
fire, too.
>> Uh-huh.
And she's very gullible to that.
She doesn't do anything at all.
>> No, she doesn't do anything
at all.
>> No, she doesn't.
>> If you think about it, I
mean, we could lose Eliza over
Chris first, you know.
>> That's true.
>> Was Scout in your final four?
>> Originally. I mean, in my
head, I never said it out loud.
I think I'm tending to lean
toward more of the three other
people that I'd want to see in
the final four versus that I
want to see...
>> I know that's the dilemma.
Yeah, like being with, like,
Eliza and Scout, and...
>> I don't think I'd like that.
>> Everyone would be deserving.
So I'd be down.
I'd be faithful.
>> Yeah?
>> I would, completely.
>> I never promised Scout
anything, and all Scout ever
asked was to be let known she
was going to go, and I don't
have a problem with her being
fifth.
( laughing )
>> Cheers.
>> That was fun.
Little one, look at you.
She's all pissed off.
>> Today's reward challenge, I
was really annoyed.
I felt that there were two women
in particular, Scout and Twila,
who were after me, and Scout
kind of said "Oh, little one,
get over it; it's just a game."
But it was more being taken out
in that way-- it is personal.
It's definitely personal.
>> Oh, Eliza, good grief.
It is not.
In this game, you've got to take
out the smartest people.
>> For some reason, I
feel like you're saying that and
it's, like, condescending.
Are you being serious?
>> Of course I'm being serious.
>> You are smart.
>> Yeah, this whole thing
is just a game, Scout's right,
but gosh, if she wasn't here one
more day, I would be a happy
camper.
>> How can you say that?
I said, "In deference to your
brilliance."
That's exactly the truth.
I've been fed up with Eliza
since Day Two.
I'm totally over her.
>> The challenge definitely
showed vulnerability in the
women's alliance.
Questions arose in their minds
as to, you know, where do they
stand.
Eliza did realize about the
pecking order, and, um, she
didn't like it.
We see a weakness right there.
So it definitely opened up some
doors for us to look into.
Eliza is definitely in doubt of
her position with the girls, and
she is vulnerable.
Scout don't like Eliza already.
Scout will burn Eliza.
>> Yeah.
There's no place for Eliza in
their final plan.
>> Exactly.
She just doesn't seem like a
power player.
>> She's a token player in
Ami and Scout's game.
>> We've got to take Eliza out.
We have got to totally sabotage
Eliza's game and send her home.
One of the ideas we come up out
there was to try to convince the
women that Eliza feels
vulnerable, that she doesn't
trust her position, that she's
unhappy with when she was
selected in that challenge and
that possibly she's been talking
to us about jumping over with
us.
( laughing )
>> There it is!
>> I can see it.
>> Oh, my God!
( whooping )
Put your window down.
Wave your hand all the way out
there.
>> There they are. They're...
they are waving.
>> Our girls are back.
( whooping )
>> Oh, they got a bundle
in their hands.
>> They're gone. They're away.
( whooping )
Are you wasted? Get over here.
>> Yes, we're wasted, but
we smuggled only you ladies back
something.
>> Oh, God.
>> Shh, shh.
Okay, we got chicken wings for
you, we got bones for them.
>> Two... we have two chicken
wings for each of you.
>> Quick...
>> Give them her... give
them their chicken wings.
>> Julie lifts up her pants and
she had tied a bag of leftover
chicken wings to her leg.
>> Oh, my God.
( Scout gasps )
>> Here you go. Run.
Not a word. Not a word. Run.
( talking quietly )
>> Oh, my God.
>> I feel like such a, like, a
bad kid.
>> I know.
>> Man.
>> Don't waste a drop, dude.
Eat the fat.
Eat everything but the bone.
Isn't it yummy, though?
>> Did you all stuff yourself?
You got plenty?
>> Yeah.
>> Eat the cartilage.
>> You eat that.
>> All right.
>> I mean, that's more than just
a...
>> I know.
>> Ready, go.
>> The girls are back.
You are drunk.
>> Did you put the bones in?
>> The bones?
>> Put the bones in.
>> Oh, is there any meat on the
bones?
>> We just didn't know
what would be offensive and
insulting or whatever, so...
>> And all we could do is
bring back the bones.
>> No kidding?
You brought back chicken bones?
>> Oh, my God.
I seen my bone. I see my bone.
Look at that meat on that bone.
>> Uh-huh.
I was real pleased that they
brought back some bones of hot
wings.
The average American would be
like "Oh, my God, that is the
lowest form of insult I could
ever imagine," but to the Alinta
tribe, it was like Christmas.
>> So, listen, you guys rock...
>> Yeah?
>> ...for bringing back these
bones.
>> Yeah, thanks for
bringing this back, you guys.
>> We were, like, "Are
they gonna get insulted?"
But I was, like, "I would want
to eat the bones."
>> It is not insulting at all.
>> Look how insulted we look.
>> The guys-- when they
came back-- were really excited
about getting the bones, and we
had to pretend to be excited
about the bones, too, because
they didn't know that we had
just had chicken wings.
>> Wow.
>> We... Yeah, we tried to...
>> We tried to leave meat.
>> Julie and I were just
kind of sitting there watching
everybody, going, "Oh, man, if
they only knew."
>> Thanks, girls.
Life is good at Alinta.
( birds singing)
>> This is fun...
Oh.
( snorting)
No way.
( laughs)
I went to get tree mail alone
this morning, and then there
sitting tied up right behind
tree mail was this big pig.
Come on, buddy.
I've never really dealt with
animals.
I've never, you know, been
around a farm.
Why don't you want to go?
No, come on.
Piggy.
Come on.
Why are you being so difficult?
Shh. It's okay.
( snorting)
Piggy, come on.
I don't want to drag you the
whole way, come on.
( squealing)
Chris, Chris!
Tree mail.
Help, come here.
( Chris muttering)
>> No. Oh, my God.
Of course I had to go to this
tree mail.
Okay, piggy. Help is coming.
( squealing)
>> There's a pig.
( indistinct chatter )
>> Oh, yeah.
Nice and steady...
>> Thank you.
>> Here, pig, pig, pig...
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
You can't eat him. Don't...
You both have machetes.
Good start.
>> Come on, Sarge.
>> Wait, listen, listen, listen.
>> I'm ready to eat.
>> We want bacon. We don't care
about this damn pig.
>> Here, pig, pig, pig, pig,
pig.
I wanted to eat the pig so bad
that I could taste his
fatback cooked up with my
cabbages.
>> "Health, wealth, a status
symbol.
With this pig, you could have it
made.
Feed him, clean him, take good
care, give him shelter in the
shade.
Soon enough some of you will
learn the value of this pig, so
keep him happy, healthy and in
your camp.
Soon he could pay off big."
>> Yeah. I still...
>> He still looks awful damn
good to me.
>> He still looks...
( Twila laughs)
>> He still looks like ribs.
I read this note. It says, "No,
can't kill the pig."
It was a big letdown.
It was about as big a letdown as
when I found out Estrogen City
was moving into Lopevi.
You don't know how much I want
to eat you.
If I can't link myself to the
Estrogen City, at least I can
link myself to a pig.
( pig snorts )
You know?
Have some friend up in here.
>> PROBST: Wow, Sarge, you look
angry.
>> Just thinking.
>> PROBST: Good or bad, immunity
is back up for grabs.
I'll get that from you.
All right, for today's
challenge, you're gonna start
with a puzzle.
You'll have a minute to complete
the puzzle.
Each round, I will give you a
different configuration of that
puzzle.
Get it right, you stay in.
Wrong, you're out.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, is safe from the vote
tonight.
Everybody else, fair game.
Simple enough?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Completely random,
take a spot behind one of the
puzzles.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
The first puzzle configuration.
Yeah, wait.
Right now you're just looking,
making notes.
Begin.
30 seconds.
15 seconds.
Five, four...
three, two...
one.
Everybody take your hands off
your puzzle board.
All right, everybody turn your
puzzle board around to face me.
Eliza got it right.
>> Is this blue?
>> PROBST: Chad's wrong.
Ami's right.
Julie got it right.
Leann got it right.
Scout got it right.
Twila got it right.
Chris, you have it wrong.
( Chris sighs )
>> Wrong.
>> PROBST: Sarge, you have it
wrong.
Chad, Chris, Sarge-- all the
men, all wrong.
Take a seat on the bench.
First round down, three men
gone.
Next puzzle configuration.
Begin.
30 seconds.
Ten seconds.
Five, four...
three, two...
one.
Take your hands off your
puzzles.
All right, turn 'em around.
Eliza got it right.
Still in.
Ami got it right.
She's still good.
Julie's right.
Leann's right.
Scout's wrong.
And Twila's wrong.
Round two is over.
Scout and Twila, take a seat on
the log.
We are down to four.
Next puzzle configuration.
This time you'll get less time
to look at it and less time to
put it together.
Begin.
30 seconds.
Last ten seconds.
Five, four...
three, two, one.
Take your hands off your puzzle.
Spin 'em around.
Eliza, you have a worried look
on your face.
>> I might have messed something
up.
>> PROBST: What do you think you
might have messed up?
Nope, but you messed something
else up.
>> I did?
>> PROBST: You're wrong.
Ami got it right.
Julie got it right.
Leann got it right.
Eliza the only casualty in that
round.
We are down to three.
Next puzzle configuration.
We're going to shorten the time
even more.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Go.
20 seconds.
Ami caught something right at
the end.
Five, four.
Leann hustling.
Three, two, one.
You're done.
Spin them around.
Ami what did you change at the
last?
>> I had to turn these to blue.
I mean, to green.
>> PROBST: Ami's right.
Julie's wrong.
Leann.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You're wrong.
>> Oh, come on now.
>> PROBST: Ami wins immunity.
( applause and cheering )
Face your tribe.
Only one person safe tonight at
the vote.
That is this woman, Ami.
Everybody else is fair game.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who's going home tonight.
I will see you all at Tribal
Council.
Head on back to camp.
>> I'm pissed off at myself that
I didn't expect the center spike
to be different colors, and I
look at it, and I'm like oh, my
God.
>> I won the challenge today.
I don't know if that was the
smartest idea in the world, just
because I'm already kind of seen
as a stronger woman, and that's
a threat to some of the other
women, but I can't let myself
play bad.
>> I'm glad you won.
How about if I win all the
rewards and you win all the
immunity?
>> Okay. Oh, I like that!
>> Works for me!
>> Tonight at Tribal Council,
I'm voting for Sarge.
He's a strong physical threat
and out of other guys it's
probably best that we send him
first since he doesn't have
immunity now.
>> Basically, I get the
feeling that I'm going home
because of a physical threat,
but I actually think that there
can be a twist and Eliza could
go home because Scout is that
much against her.
>> Okay. We're ready.
>> Grab the box, the crate.
>> What box do we need?
>> The crate right up there.
>> Of course, little Liza, I
hate hanging out with that
energy.
>> It's true.
We always imagined that she was
the first because she's already
been on the chopping block, and
that's common knowledge, so...
>> Well, just me personally.
She drives me nutty.
If she says that word "like" a
thousand times, just drives me
nutty.
>> Scout is out plotting with
them right now.
I don't know if they will take
her word again, but after she...
( Ami chuckles )
>> I... it's so funny.
>> She talks so much ( bleep )
about you and about me and it's
just like...
>> I think it's funny.
>> Now she's trying to get back
in with Chris and just like...
>> She's good at it.
She's good at it though.
>> I feel like I've been
paranoid since day one.
I mean, it's a game where people
are going to be voting each
other off so you have to be
paranoid.
She's the only person here who I
really have a strong dislike
for.
Scout has already gone after me
two, three times now.
I think she would write my name
down in a heartbeat, and, you
know, I would write her name
down in a heartbeat.
>> Eliza and myself have
an ongoing tension, you know.
She knows that she annoys me,
and I'm sure I annoy her so
that's going on.
And I think something else might
be going on.
Jules and Leann have gotten to
be kind of tight since they went
on their little trip together,
and I think Leann might have
bumped me down in the hierarchy
a little bit after that trip.
So there may be some changes.
Hell, I might get sent home
tonight.
>> I didn't screw you all on
purpose.
That's the way I felt: that you
were getting ready to ... me
over after Julie...
Would you not have got the
damn same feeling, Sarge?
>> No.
>> Why?
>> 'Cause you gave me your word.
>> I did give...
>> You gave me your word, Twila.
And I would have walked off this
game today before I crossed your
word.
I'll be honest with you.
This is how it was supposed to
go.
It was supposed to go Rory, then
you, then Chad, Chris and me.
>> But I'd have been a fourth
person.
>> You were four so solid, like
my whole life depended on it.
>> Blame it on Julie that
the reason things got changed.
Today was the first day that I
actually got to talk to Sarge
alone, and I thought the guys
were manipulating me, but Sarge
looked at me and told me
honestly, and I believe him
wholeheartedly, that Julie put
doubt in my mind against the
guys.
She's going to bump me and Scout
out, I can feel it already.
>> I know, that's what I'm
saying, that's why me and Chris
are sick to our stomach, and we
kept saying, "Where did Twila
think she was?
She had a guaranteed four slot."
>> But I didn't know that.
How did I know that anymore with
you?
>> Why didn't you come to me
again after Julie talked to
you and looked me in the eye and
I would have swore to you?
>> I should have, Sarge.
I screwed up when I didn't vote
with the guys.
I felt uneasy about making the
decision I made because I've had
more respect out of these three
guys I felt than I ever got over
at the girls' camp, there's no
doubt about it, and I do feel
like I let 'em down.
>> Yeah.
>> Remember that time we
were talking about in the boat?
I just thought of it.
If you three, us three, Twila
and if we got Eliza, 'cause
she's next on the chopping
block, it would be 5-4.
If she, has any brains at
all, I just thought of this.
>> Chad said if I went on
their side and they could get
Eliza to go with us, we could
knock the women out.
I'm willing to play however I
have to play this game to get
ahead, I'm gonna play it.
>> In this game your strategy
changes just immediately, and
since the ladies got here, I
learned real quick from the
first night that you got to
watch what you say, that they
are a tight-knit group and if
you want to survive, you're
going to have to please them.
I've been in alliance with Sarge
and Chad since day one.
We don't have the numbers.
Unless we can pull something off
with Twila and Eliza, it's over.
>> PROBST: Well, over the last
couple of days a lot of emotion
has been wearing on the sleeve.
I want to talk about a little
of it starting with yesterday's
reward challenge, and you,
Eliza, you were the first woman
knocked out and when you sat
down on the bench with the guys,
you weren't hiding anything.
>> I was pissed.
What can I say?
I mean, I would have been pissed
if I was the second to last
person knocked out, too.
I mean, it's just my nature.
>> PROBST: The reason I bring it
up is dating back as far as I
think the very first Tribal
Council, it seems like you've
been struggling with this group
of women.
Are you still fighting a little
bit?
>> I'm the only woman
tonight who came with a bag
packed because even when I
think that it's absolutely
certain I don't want to have,
you know, Rory syndrome and
start to feel confident and then
get booted, so, yes.
This is a game.
It's always on my mind.
I always feel vulnerable.
>> PROBST: Sarge, are you
starting to sense some division
within the women?
>> Oh, I mean, there is
division, I see it every day.
There's a four-way and there's a
two-way here, and if they would
jump away from that group and
take that chance, maybe they
have a better shot at something
later.
People make decisions on a spur-
of-the-moment thing.
You know, you tell them the
wrong thing.
That's what happened with Twila.
I told her no matter what,
you're the number four in my
pack.
Well, Jules went to her and said
she was promised number four and
Twila automatically freaked out
and thought that Jules had got
her a number four slot and Twila
was out to lunch, so she jumped
back with the women.
>> I felt that I was
being played all the way around.
>> Yeah, she felt she was being,
she let Julie, uh, snake her.
>> I was stuck in the
middle, and I think the women
know I felt more at ease over
here with the men than I ever
did with the women.
I'm not going to lie about that,
and it's tough.
>> PROBST: Leann, is there a
certain amount of respect for
Twila that she's being honest in
saying, "Yeah, I did make
friends on both side;
I'm not going to lie about it;
and I'm conflicted about it"?
>> Oh, absolutely, and I
think Twila kind of had the
worst position of anybody in
that the guys kind of came down
on her more than her and Julie,
for the way she voted last
Tribal Council, and I don't know
why Julie kind of got off
scot-free out of that one.
>> I was kind of curious
about that myself.
>> How did I get off scot-free?
All my skulls were put out by
the men.
They're gonna write my name down
tonight instead of Twila's.
>> PROBST: Chris, is duplicity
part of this game?
>> Yeah. It's part of this game.
When you're put in a situation
like Julie and Twila was, they
played the game, and they played
both sides.
Would I have done the same?
Probably. This game is all about
numbers, and they got the
numbers, you know, but the game
ain't over yet.
We're still playing.
>> PROBST: Okay.
With tonight's vote, the game
changes a little bit because
tonight you're voting out the
first member of your jury.
So it is not only who you vote
out, but how you vote people out
from here on out that's going to
dictate somebody's future
because seven of you will end up
over here, two of you will
end up in the final Tribal
Council, and those seven people
are going to determine which one
gets the million bucks.
Having said that, Ami, you have
the immunity necklace.
Holding on to it?
>> I am.
>> PROBST: Ami is the only
person you cannot vote for.
Everybody else is definitely
fair game, it is time to vote.
Eliza, you're up.
>> I'm going to burn every one
of them.
Just let them open the door.
This is for you, not against
you.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
Sarge.
Eliza.
Julie.
One vote Eliza, one vote Sarge.
One vote Julie.
Sarge.
Two votes Sarge.
That's three votes Sarge.
Sarge.
Four votes Sarge.
Tenth person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu: Sarge.
That's five. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Sarge, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Talk all you want about who has
the numbers advantage, but there
is one wildcard you can always
count on: individual immunity;
and that can get any one of you
all the way to the end.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> It's been raining forever.
>> It's going to be a
miracle if we can keep our fire.
I've never been in a worse
situation than this.
>> PROBST: And then Scout makes
her move.
>> The guys will vote with us,
then the game changes.
>> Right now I'm not real
trusting in the ladies.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> I just want to say
I enjoyed myself.
I had an experience of a
lifetime to all the people in
the game, changed my character
and put another chip in my
foundation of what I believe in.
I never had to jeopardize my
word, my character and my name,
so good luck to you all, and I
would not want to be here there
while y'all tear each other's
head off.