>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor: 18 castaways were
marooned on the island nation of
Vanuatu, and during a native
ceremony, the men and women were
divided into opposing tribes.
>> It's perfect.
I can outsmart eight men a hell
of a lot quicker than I can
outsmart eight women.
>> PROBST: The pressure was on
when the men were given a chance
to get a traditional spirit
stone for luck.
You have to get it from the top
of that pole.
If you fail, the women get it.
Brady got the stone for the men.
>> I think the boys got a
lot more out of that ceremony
than we did.
We're out for blood now.
>> PROBST: On the hike to find
their camp, conflict came quick
to the Yasur tribe when Scout
held back the others.
>> I just wanted to
hunker down till daylight.
>> Like, I think sleeping
right here is, like, the
stupidest thing we could
possibly do.
>> PROBST: And for Lopevi, it
was Rory who stirred the pot.
>> We really need to come
up with some sort of game plan.
Nine of us walking in a group
like a bunch of ladies ain't
helping.
>> PROBST: Both tribes found
their camps.
>> We got the flag!
(cheering)
>> PROBST: And the next morning
at Yasur, there was more
division.
>> Twila has been working
on the shelter constantly.
>> We had too much chatting
and not enough moving.
>> I call these sorority
girls "bowheads."
They all like to hang together.
They're like cattle.
>> I'm really not a
negative person, like...
>> Eliza talks non-stop.
She's probably at the top of my
list just to get her mouth out
of my face.
>> PROBST: At the first
challenge, the men and women
competed for immunity as well as
flint to make fire.
Lopevi had the lead, until Chris
failed to make it across the
balance beam.
The women win the war and
immunity!
Back at camp, the younger guys
wanted Chris out.
>> PROBST: But Chris and Lea had
their own plan.
>> The only way we're going
to get a million dollars-- one
of us-- is if we get rid of the
young people.
>> I'll talk to Chad.
I'll take care of it.
>> PROBST: Lea and Chris's plan
worked.
Perceived as a physical threat
by the older men, Brook was
voted out of the tribe.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(bird chirping)
>> Last night was
freezing cold.
The standing joke this morning
was, "Well, how was your sleep
this morning?"
My answer was, "I slept like a
baby.
Woke up every three or four
minutes and cried."
It's not good.
We need fire for heat and just
for food, 'cause we're getting
so drained.
I want to eat something cooked
so bad.
>> Look, I'll eat it.
I mean, it's protein.
>> It's been pretty
tough... a lot tougher than I
thought it would be.
Are we prepared for fire if it
does actually take off?
Have we got everything we need
to keep it going?
Nothing positive's really
happened for us.
We need something to boost our
morale.
>> All right, dawg.
>> This could change everything.
>> We're ready.
This is it.
It smells good already.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Keep going.
>> Good smoke.
>> Ready?
>> It's getting darker.
>> Go, go, go!
>> Come on, J.P.,
go, dude, go.
Go, dude.
Come on, dude, come on.
More heat, the more fire, dude.
Go, dude, go, dude.
Keep it going, J.P.
>> It's hot.
Oh, yeah, it is.
>> Real light, real light and
slow.
Steady, steady, steady.
Real light and slow.
>> We got it.
Get it in there.
>> It's lit. It's lit.
It's lit. It is lit.
>> It's burning my hand
underneath.
>> Come here, Sarge, quick!
Nobody blow.
Just let Chris, okay?
>> Cover it up. Make it more.
>> Ow! Man, that thing burnt
my hand.
>> It's going to take off.
>> Pay tribute.
Pay tribute.
>> It's going to start.
>> Respect the island.
Respect the island.
>> That's it, Chris.
>> Whoever gets to be around.
>> It's smoking!
>> Get away from it with that.
>> Whoo!
>> It's raining.
It just can't rain.
>> We need something drier.
We need...
>> It's too hot.
(shouts)
>> Cover it up.
>> Keep it hot.
Keep it hot.
>> Come on, come on, catch!
>> Nothing, dude.
>> You know, we're working
ourselves to death, and, uh...
that was a real downer.
We know exactly that if we don't
get water soon, we're going to
be hurting.
These girls are going to kick
our tail.
>> We don't mind spotting you.
>> Go ahead. We got you.
>> Now, go up first.
>> Now step on my shoulder.
>> Got it?
>> Got it.
>> All right, yeah, you can
get it?
>> Get her the machete!
>> Wait, I can't do it.
You got to do it together.
>> Keep her on your shoulder.
>> One, two, three, up.
>> Yeah.
Here it comes.
Oh, geez, the machete.
>> Please don't drop the
machete, dude.
>> Lift me up a little bit
higher.
>> You better hurry up.
>> Yeah, honey, I-I can't...
>> I can't do much more
of this.
>> Get it!
>> You're on my hand.
>> Wait! (grunts)
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm going to grab it.
>> Yes!
>> Yay!
>> Good job, mama.
>> I'm going to tell you what.
This better be good for dinner.
>> That better not be
poisonous.
Day four.
It's going rough.
It's just getting unreal-- the
circumstances and our living
conditions.
And it's about 1,000 times
harder than I thought this was
going to be.
(thunder rumbling)
Gosh, can we get a break here,
man?
>> It's just... horrendous.
The beach is uncomfortable.
The water's uncomfortable.
It's freezing at night.
Everything is damp.
Like, you always feel wet and
cold.
I mean, it's beautiful, like,
looking at it, but, like, to
live here, it's just so
miserable.
I think someone was saying last
night that being here is like
being in prison, because we do
not have nearly enough food, and
then we have these unripe,
disgusting plantains that when
you cook 'em just taste like
burnt... mush.
>> How's the coconut cooked?
>> Uh-oh.
>> What is that, a maggot?
>> Yep.
>> Here, hand it over.
>> Oh, my God, there are maggots
in that.
>> There are a bunch of
'em in there.
>> Oh, my God, I see them.
>> Where?
>> They're all over.
>> It can't be a maggot,
because it's...
it's-it's been boiled.
>> Are those maggots, Scout?
>> Those are definitely maggots.
>> Eh, I'm eating it anyway.
Everything was boiled.
>> Boy, look at all that
protein in there.
>> Yeah, eat 'em up, mm.
Gosh, give 'em to me. Mm...
>> Just not eating and
not sleeping at night, and
the... the maggots...
And it's just all sinking in.
It's... it's rough.
Nothing's wrong. It's just...
it's just coming out of me.
>> You've been crying.
>> (sighs)
But nothing's wrong.
I'm just... it's just coming
out of me.
(sighs)
Like, I'm having fun.
I'm not... I'm not complaining
at all.
I'm so happy to be here.
I just am hungry and tired.
>> Eliza, do you know why
somebody put the...?
>> Thank you.
You are so nice to me.
(sighs)
>> I don't know.
These young ones-- I don't know
if they thought this was a joke.
I don't know what they was
thinking.
If it comes down to eating
maggots, I'm going to eat
maggots.
To me, if there was,
they were cooked.
They're good. Protein.
Eat 'em. Shut up.
Sorority girls, like... like
Scout calls 'em-- they're not
mature enough.
They're not physically strong
enough.
They just...
they just wear me out.
They just don't understand the
game, I guess.
If they want to be pampered,
they need to go back to the
Holiday Inn.
>> Travis, can I ask
you something personal?
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> Before Tribal Council,
did my name come up?
>> This past one?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Yes, it did.
>> Tribal Council last
night was very intense, and it
was an eye-opener.
As of right now, it's myself,
John and Brady.
We're kind of like the physical,
young, vibrant guys in the
tribe.
Then you have the older crowd:
the Sarge, Chad, Rory, Travis
and Chris.
Those are five guys.
Right now, it's five against
three.
Those aren't good odds.
>> I'll shoot you straight.
Let's stop and talk, all right?
>> Let's stop and talk, man.
>> You're too big of a threat.
>> Okay.
>> I like you.
>> Great.
>> I think... I think...
>> Wait, a threat to
the group or a threat to you?
>> When this thing...
when this thing goes, it's your
personality, your great looks.
That's a threat.
When I make my decision, I've
got four children at home
and a wife.
And that's what I base my
decisions on.
You are so frickin' dangerous,
man.
>> So if I had kids, would
that... would that alter
your decision?
Is that what you're telling me?
>> No, I'm saying, if
you had kids, you'd be playing
the game and understand...
>> What, like-like you?
I'd be playing the game like you
if I had kids?
>> I've known you for
what now, five days?
>> Five days. Five days.
>> I've got a family at
home I've known a long time.
>> Five days.
Who else is a threat, T.?
>> Anybody playing the game.
>> Yeah?
>> Anybody that's in this game.
There were 17 threats when we
started this game.
17 threats.
Only one person wins.
>> PROBST: Yasur coming in nine
strong.
Hey, guys.
Yasur getting your first look at
the new Lopevi Tribe.
>> Who's gone?
>> PROBST: Brook-- voted out,
first Tribal Council.
Ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Okay, it's for
reward.
Here's how it works:
Each tribe member, numbered one
through eight, will line up on a
beam.
Moving one tribe member at a
time, in order, you move down
the beam, squeezing past the
other tribe members.
If you fall off, go back to the
start.
Keep trying until you get it
right.
You cannot touch more than one
person at any time.
If you do, go back to the start,
try again.
First tribe to get all eight to
the finish platform wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Hopefully, this will
help...
(excited chattering)
...your night sleeping a little
better.
(exclaiming)
Okay, you have one hammock,
two pillows,
three nice heavy, heavy
blankets.
In addition, Lopevi, from here
on out, you'll also be playing
for your flint.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Yasur, because you
have one extra tribe member,
you're sitting somebody out.
You cannot sit out the same
person in back-to-back
challenges.
Who is sitting out, Yasur?
>> Scout.
>> PROBST: Scout's going to sit
this one out.
All right, take your spots on
the beam-- wait for my go.
Here we go, guys.
For reward in the form of
blankets and pillows and for the
men, the chance for fire.
Survivors, ready and begin.
You can only touch one person at
a time.
Bye-bye.
Back to the start.
Resist the temptation to touch
two people.
That's it.
Eliza, back to the beginning.
Brady making his way past one.
Eliza and Lisa struggling.
Nice and close.
Brady starting to figure it out.
Moving past Chad.
Brady and Chad doing well.
Eliza moving past Dolly.
Don't touch two people.
Brady moving past Sarge.
As you get room, spread out a
little more.
Eliza is down.
>> Yes! Go, go, go!
Come on, Yasur!
>> PROBST: Bubba and Brady doing
a little waltz.
Not sure Bubba likes this.
>> It's okay.
Come on, come on.
>> PROBST: Julie's in.
Brady only one spot away.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: And he's there.
All the way down.
>> Julie, come on.
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: J.K. moving past J.P.
Holding that hug just a little
long.
J.K. and J.P. still struggling.
Julie's finished.
The women have two across.
The men still at one.
John talking through it with
Sarge.
>> You have to trust each
other.
If you lean back, he'll hold
you.
Trust him.
>> Way to go, way to go!
>> PROBST: John goes in.
>> Nice, nice, nice.
>> PROBST: Taking Twila a long
time.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Twila's across.
That's four for the women.
And the men still at one.
>> We want them damn
blankets.
I'm freezing my butt off.
>> John, you're going
with them, buddy.
>> PROBST: Brady trying to help.
...back, John!
Chad, you've got to trust...
you've got to trust that he'll
hold you, buddy.
You have to lean back a little
farther.
>> PROBST: Ooh.
>> Way to go, Twila.
You're looking good.
>> PROBST: No, Ami.
Back to the start.
You touched two people at one
time.
>> Just jump and go.
>> PROBST: John's past Chad,
moving on to Sarge.
>> Take your time, Ami.
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: That's the way, John.
Moving past Bubba.
John back in.
Ami across.
Five women, one man.
Leann gets past Dolly easily.
Pillows, blankets, hammock at
stake for the women.
Women down to the last two.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Dolly steps down.
Mia moonwalks over to the side.
(woman cheering)
Yasur wins their second
challenge in a row!
(cheering loudly)
(women whooping)
All right, well, guys, once
again balance beam proves tough.
You were playing for flint in
addition.
That will stay with me.
You'll get a chance at the next
challenge.
Guys, head on out, back to camp.
Same way you came.
Women, this is yours.
(cheering)
>> Could you imagine Sarge
getting past Travis?
It's impossible.
>> And Twila's little dance.
(humming)
What the hell... what is that?
>> That wasn't Twila.
>> Well, whatever her name
is.
>> Mia.
>> It was a game.
I mean, we lost.
>> At least show some class,
man.
>> (stammers)
>> We probably would've
done...
>> I understand that
they're proud about it, Sarge.
>> But we would've done the
same thing.
>> No, I don't think that
we would've done the same thing.
I don't think that we would've
intentionally shoved somebody's
nose into it.
You know, that was nonsense.
That was classless.
Show some class!
They're grown women.
I understand it's a competition,
but if she was a man, would you
have taken that, Sarge?
No.
>> Take what?
I mean, we lost.
I mean, I lose humble because
it's a competition.
>> I'm humbled because of
that, too, but I don't need a
dance.
>> Okay.
I have been contemplating over
this one person that is striking
me wrong as rain.
>> Yeah.
>> Same person.
>> And I'm like, man,
I just... I'm... we're in a
game.
And to sit there and defame
someone because of a game, you
know, how you going to get
upset?
I mean, he's all, "Well, they
shouldn't have danced."
But to sit there and walk around
here and grumble for hours over
something...
It's just, I don't know, it...
strikes me funny.
>> I think we're going to
have a sunny day.
>> Good morning.
♪ Good morning to you
Good morning to you. ♪
(humming)
>> I am just happy that
we have water and we had
blankets last night, and the
guys are suffering big time.
And I wouldn't want to be in
their shoes because I know what
it was like the first couple
days and that sucks, big time.
(clucking)
>> Don't move, don't move.
>> You guys, I have never
killed anything.
>> My shoes aren't...
Wait, don't move, don't move.
He's going to go that way.
I want him to come this way.
You can't run after it because
the thing will fly.
(clucking continues)
Just don't scare him away the
other way.
>> Chicken soup sure
sounded good.
>> Chicken soup?
Man, the whole chicken.
(clucking)
>> Just swing down and
thump him.
(clucking)
>> I'll tell you what.
I'll kill that rooster if I
find it.
(clucking)
>> Oh, I see him.
Oh, my God, he's laying an egg.
>> "She."
I hate to be mean but...
>> What are you going to do?
(clucking)
>> I could go right
through here.
>> I say just stab her.
>> It will be gross.
>> Solid stab.
>> Just do it.
Just do it.
>> Oh, God, I hate to do
this.
>> Take a deep breath, say
you're sorry, thank you, God,
for this gift.
>> Yeah, really.
>> Thank God for this
gift.
But I'm sorry, chicken, 'cause
I can't stand to hurt any
animal.
God.
(clucking)
Ooh, get her, get her!
Get her, get her!
Grab her, grab her!
Grab her!
Aah!
>> Well, is there an egg?
>> There's several eggs.
>> There's several eggs!
>> Yeah.
We almost had us a chicken.
I got five eggs.
>> Onesy... twosey...
>> Oh, this is a blessing,
y'all.
(whooping)
(gasping)
>> Careful.
>> Whoa, no.
No, no, no.
>> What happened?
>> Oh, no, oh, no.
>> The good news about
being a tribe of all women is
that we care about each other,
we want each other to succeed.
We haven't had to start voting
people off yet.
And I think we can win the next
challenge.
But I definitely see groups
forming.
The two groups that were formed
I think are like the older
generation and then the younger
generation.
That diversity in age has really
separated everybody.
>> Can you get it?
>> I think so.
It's heavy, but I got it.
>> The younger group would
be Mia, Julie, Dolly, Eliza and
Lisa, which I think she likes
being in the younger group.
And the older group has been
more like Scout and Twila, and I
think Leann's more in the older
group.
>> I just, every time I
hear 35 I think, half of 70.
I'm almost 70.
(laughing)
>> I think I gravitate more
towards the older group just
because they're really willing
to work.
But this is a game of non-trust.
I view the first day coming in,
do not trust anyone.
Don't trust anybody.
>> Well, it's going to
come down to a point not where
who likes who but who is
threatened by who.
Do you know I mean?
>> Yeah, but that's why I
say if we can get down to five
women, then the strategy's over.
>> And the girls go.
>> Yeah, and then we're
safe.
>> Twila is just wanting
to know that she is part of a
majority group.
That she's, uh, she's not on
the chopping block.
At first, we were all talking
about you.
>> I know.
>> And-and then, uh...
I think Twila knew that the five
younger girls-- and we had said
that if we had gone to Tribal
Council the first, uh, challenge
that we would have voted for
her.
And then now, you know, we
cannot vote for Twila.
She's busting her ass.
We absolutely have to have her
here.
The expendable person really is
Eliza.
>> She drives me nuts.
>> She's driving everybody...
if she's driving Scout nuts,
I mean...
>> If it comes down to
alliance-wise and stuff, it's
Ami and me and Scout and Leann.
The only one we have to worry
about is, uh, Dolly.
Dolly's going to be the...
She's the pivot person in the
middle.
I think she's in, but you never
know.
>> Yeah, let them do
their own thing.
If we got five voting for Eliza,
then we're in the clear.
>> That's it.
>> I'm-I'm with you.
Eliza.
>> Mail for you, buddy.
"So far, it seems the spirits
haven't responded to the stone.
"Depend upon your tribe mates.
You can't do this on your own.
"When you put it all together,
it takes agility, skill and
trust.
Tonight, the dreams of victory
for one will turn to dust."
>> Tree mail!
The spirit stone, is, of course,
the, uh, idol that we won on our
first welcome to the island, and
it's supposed to bring good luck
to the bearer, but quite
frankly, it has not worked for
us.
We haven't won immunity yet.
>> We need some sort of
victory around here.
>> We'll get one.
We all got to work together.
We know that.
>> The stone is important
for us.
It started off, uh, as a stone
at the ceremony.
We just brought it with us to
set up our camp, but then we
started sort of neglecting it,
and things weren't going our
way, so, um, we started to give
it a bit more respect.
>> Remember the rain when
you took it down?
>> I don't know if it's
just sick timing, but the day
has been clear all day, and then
all of a sudden, they put the
spirit stone back on the pole,
and it starts raining again.
There's magic on Vanuatu.
That's... There's magic on this
island.
>> PROBST: Yasur, Lopevi, come
on in!
All right.
Let's get to today's challenge.
I will take back immunity.
I know you hate to see it go.
>> We'll get it back.
>> PROBST: Immunity back up for
grabs.
Today's challenge is going to
test communication and the
ability to work together.
Scattered out in the field and
in the water are 12 pairs of
puzzle pieces.
You're going to designate one
tribe member to be your set of
eyes.
The other tribe members will be
blindfolded and tied together in
three groups.
You'll collect the pairs of
puzzle pieces one pair
at a time.
Bring 'em back, drop 'em on
your mat.
Once you have all the pieces
collected, take off your
blindfold, start assembling
three puzzles in order from
bottom to top.
First tribe to complete all
three puzzle wins immunity.
And for Lopevi...
>> Fire!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: You're still playing
for that flint.
Okay. Yasur, you have one extra
member.
You're sitting somebody out.
Who's it going to be?
>> Dolly.
>> PROBST: Dolly's going to sit
sit out.
>> I'll sit out.
>> PROBST: Who's going to be
your set of eyes?
>> Scout.
>> PROBST: Scout's going to be
the eyes-- Lopevi?
>> Sarge.
>> PROBST: Sarge is going
to be the eyes.
All right, let's get you
blindfold, and we'll get going.
Here we go, guys, for immunity,
and Lopevi, for flint.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> J.P., forward 15 paces.
J.P., forward.
Chad, go, Chad, keep going.
Keep going. Bubba, ten o'clock.
Ten o'clock.
>> Pick it up.
You unhook it. Unhook it.
>> Go straight ahead!
Lean down. Pick that up.
Pick that up.
>> Here, I got something.
Come on. Turn around.
>> Bubba, come to me.
Right here.
>> Ow!
>> This way! Sideways!
Sideways! Back up. Drop it.
>> PROBST: Yasur has their
first piece.
Lopevi has their first piece.
Looking for 12 pairs.
But a traffic jam with Yasur.
>> Come on, come here.
>> J.P., stop!
J.P., nine o'clock.
Nine o'clock. Okay.
Six o'clock, J.P.
Six o'clock.
Six o'clock, J.P.!
>> Yo, Sarge.
>> Help!
>> Water team, go
straight, go straight.
You're doing great.
>> Right in front of you.
Keep walking, keep walking.
Right there!
>> PROBST: Lopevi with their
second pair.
Left! Straight, Bubba. Left.
To the left. To the left.
Right there.
>> Keep going, keep going.
>> PROBST: Yasur with five
pairs.
>> One, two, three.
>> Scout!
>> Hey, water team, go right.
>> J.P., left! J.P., left!
Straight! Go straight!
Feel it? That's you!
>> Good!
>> Mia, it's right behind
you, cookie.
>> It's right here.
>> You got it?
>> You guys, hurry up!
Let's go!
>> Yo, Bubba, go to the left!
Left, Bubba! Bubba, left!
No, Bubba, go to the left!
Bubba, left! Left!
Left! Now straight!
That's it!
Yeah, straight ahead!
Come on! Right here!
Straight ahead!
>> PROBST: Lopevi coming back
with two pairs.
>> Straight! Right there.
Put it down.
>> PROBST: Lopevi with eight
pairs.
Yasur at five, falling behind.
Yasur with their sixth pair.
>> What else?
>> Turn around.
>> Come on!
>> Brady, straight ahead!
>> Ow!
>> PROBST: Brady took one on the
shin.
>> You're all right, man.
You're all right. Just breathe.
>> This way.
Feel the path right there.
You're on it.
>> You got to lead us.
We can't hear you out there.
>> J.P., left, to the left!
>> Water team, you're
going to pick one up right there
in a minute.
>> Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
>> PROBST: Ooh!
>> There it is.
All right.
>> PROBST: Lopevi with their
eleventh pair.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Lopevi needs one
more pair.
>> Ami, go straight ahead.
>> Feel in front of me
and stuff, 'cause you
never know.
Oh, my God.
>> To the left, J.P.!
Left! Right there!
Left! Left!
That's it! Come to me!
>> Go straight.
Come on, come to my voice.
Come to my voice.
>> PROBST: This is nine and ten
for Yasur.
>> Sarge, we'll direct
them, Sarge.
We'll direct them.
>> You need to stay still
and be quiet!
>> Lopevi!
>> Stay!
>> Stay, J.P.!
Stay!
>> Lopevi!
>> Hey, you, hey, stop!
Stop! You are messing me up!
Straight! Straight!
>> To your right.
Go ahead.
>> To the right.
>> I got it.
>> You got it?
>> Is this it?
>> Scout, should we go
back to the water?
>> No, we're good.
>> We don't have any more
in the water?
>> No, we got 'em.
You guys, hurry up!
Get to my voice! Let's go!
>> PROBST: Lopevi coming back
with their last pair.
>> Put it down!
>> PROBST: Get 'em off!
Take off the blindfolds!
>> Come on, guys, let's do this.
>> PROBST: Yasur coming back
with their eleventh piece.
>> Hustle. You're there.
Drop it. Take off your
blindfolds.
>> PROBST: No, Scout!
Scout!
>> We got any more?
Scout, we got any more?
>> We got one in the water.
>> I said that!
I said I thought...
>> All right, go.
Go to the water. Go.
>> Look at the yellow.
>> PROBST: Lopevi with a huge
lead.
>> Keep going, Lisa.
Reach out and get it.
Unclip it.
>> PROBST: Let's go, Yasur!
Keep moving!
Yasur, take off your blindfolds.
>> Take off your
blindfolds.
>> PROBST: Start untying.
Let's go!
>> Let's go! Untying.
>> PROBST: Lopevi taking a long
time with that first puzzle.
Yasur, you're still in this.
>> Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
>> PROBST: Lopevi has their
first puzzle complete.
Working on number two.
Yasur has their first puzzle
completed.
Moving on to number two.
>> Let's go, let's go, let's go!
>> PROBST: Lopevi moving on to
their final puzzle.
>> Hand me something.
Hand me something.
>> PROBST: The guys working
together well, talking,
communicating.
>> Right there!
That's it, that's it, that's it!
>> PROBST: Lopevi wins immunity!
(cheering)
>> I am Lopevi!
Say my name!
>> PROBST: Lopevi finally wins a
challenge.
You have immunity.
(cheering)
No Tribal Council.
>> What up? What up?
Give it here! Give it here!
>> MEN: Fire!
>> PROBST: Fire!
>> Fire! Fire!
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
Yasur, Tribal Council tonight.
You'll vote out your first
member.
Head on back.
(cheering)
>> Hey, there's no crying
on Survivor.
>> No crying in Survivor.
>> No, there's not.
>> Honey, we play 'em
well, and we play 'em tight...
>> Everything's going to be
fine.
>> Let's go...
>> We've got a coconut down here
ready to go.
>> I never expected to
like everyone so much.
>> Really?
>> It's just awful.
>> Yeah.
>> So, are you voting
with them now?
>> I'm not voting with
anyone at this point.
I'm just going to... for this
time, I'm voting, like, for her,
because I don't know who else to
vote for.
The "T" works pretty hard
right now.
>> Right.
>> Originally, we had
Dolly secure, but I think, being
as sweet as Dolly is, you know,
she, uh, you know, kind of
switched back and felt guilty.
The only good thing about...
Well, not the only good thing
about Eliza, but a great thing
about Eliza is the fact that you
tell her to do this,
and she'll do it.
I don't think she's looking out
for her best interests.
I think she's looking out for
everybody's interests, and it's
just not possible in this game.
>> Okay, so if we keep to
our first five, then we go with
Twila then, tonight, if we go...
>> Do you feel comfortable
with that, or do you want
to keep Leann, or do you
want to get...?
I mean, Leann's just kind of
like...
>> DOLLY: Yeah, Leann's...
>> I love Leann.
I love everybody, okay, but,
like, is she less of a...?
You know, 'cause Twila does work
so hard.
>> Yeah. Maybe Leann.
Yeah, my head is completely
spinning, and I'm, uh, I'm
afraid, um, at this point,
because I don't want to...
I don't want to make the
wrong choice.
I'm definitely in the middle,
and I hate that, but I-I think
I-I'm definitely more loyal to
to my younger crowd,
my younger girls.
>> Right, right.
>> 'Cause I'd have more
fun out here, I think.
>> Do you want to say
Twila or Leann?
It's up to you.
>> Let's say Leann for
the first one.
>> Okay. Leann.
>> All right. Okay.
You know, it's... I'm already...
I've got myself in a jam.
It's a cluster... cluster
you-know-what.
>> How are we going to
decide, like, now that we have
to talk about it.
I'm down with talking about it.
Like, I didn't really talk about
it before because I wasn't close
yet, you know what I mean?
>> I think, uh, I think,
uh, Julie and Mia and myself,
and I think Lisa also, are
saying Leann for this first
time.
>> Right.
>> It's so tough, you know.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I know I can vote for
Leann or Eliza, either way.
>> That's my preferred
vote is Eliza, because she's
just so, just...
>> Yeah.
Yeah, she is irritating.
>> Just so irritating.
>> Yeah, but I have Mia
and Julie saying Leann, and just
get it done and get it over
with.
>> I wish I knew their
criteria for that.
Leann doesn't complain.
She's a strong competitor.
>> There's no rhyme or
reason behind her, it's just...
>> Leann's a pretty good
worker, isn't she, or is she...?
>> I haven't even noticed.
I don't even notice Leann.
That's the thing.
For some reason, she's just not
on my radar at all.
>> Dolly told me that she
was definitely going to vote for
Leann.
I nearly dropped my teeth.
That just...
What?
>> So who are you voting
for, Leann?
>> Who am I voting for?
>> Me.
>> I don't know.
Is there, uh...
(chuckles nervously)
What's going on?
I don't know what's going on at
all.
>> I don't agree with
either one.
I just think it's turned into a
popularity contest...
>> What's the other one?
>> ...and I'm not into
that.
>> What's the other one?
Is it me?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Why me?
>> What Dolly said was,
"We'll vote Leann off now and
save Eliza for later."
And I guess it's just how the
cookie crumbles, but it's kind
of turned into this Dolly, Julie
and Mia are, like, running the
whole thing.
>> I don't like that at all.
I-I don't like that at all.
>> This is the most
interesting thing.
I swear, everyone just running
off... trying to scheme.
>> Never knowing what's
really going on.
>> Dolly is playing both
sides big time.
>> She is hard-core playing.
And, I mean, maybe we should
just vote for her.
Honest to God.
As opposed to it being one of
the two of us.
>> You'd have to talk Scout
into that.
>> Yeah, Scout and Twila
would never go for it.
>> Yes, they would.
>> They would, too.
>> They would go for it?
>> Yes.
>> At least Eliza is down
there, and they can't really be
talking...
>> Oh, yeah, true.
>> Do you have an
alliance with somebody that
you're not telling us about?
>> I don't know what to
base my vote on.
I don't know whether I should
vote for Leann, stick with my
original alliance, and, you
know, hope that they carry me
through, or I should vote off
the person who makes me really
nervous, who I don't completely
trust.
Out of all of those five girls
in that alliance that we have,
I trust Dolly the least.
>> I got so much pressure
on me from both sides, that I
just don't know what to do.
>> I know.
All I want to know is that
you're not writing my name down.
>> No.
>> I think there is a
possibility that she could vote
me off.
That she would turn on me.
I just don't want the other four
girls in that alliance to go
blindsided.
But then again, if I bring it up
to them and I tell them, look,
I'm thinking of voting out
Dolly, they're going to say, we
better just vote you out.
So I don't know what the heck to
do.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
guys is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
approach a flame and get fire.
This is part of the ritual at
Tribal Council because in this
game, fire represents your life.
When your flame is gone, so are
you.
Back in its slot.
Have a seat.
Welcome to your first Tribal
Council.
I know you guys don't want to be
here.
Before we get to the vote, let's
talk about today's challenge.
Scout, did you feel anything as
you saw the lead getting further
and further away?
>> Yeah, I definitely
feel like I blew it.
You know, I would have loved to
have done differently.
But you can't wallow in that.
You've got to step forward and,
you know, that's what we're
doing.
>> PROBST: Eliza, let's talk
about workload.
How did it fall out?
>> Everyone has their on
days and off day, I mean, except
for... except for Twila.
>> PROBST: Was Twila the only
one doing work or were there
people at the other end of the
spectrum?
Twila?
>> Oh, no, I had help.
Leann, Scout, Ami, us four did a
lot of work.
But the rest of them worked hard
in their areas, too.
>> PROBST: Leann, what's been
the toughest for you?
>> Not sleeping.
It's really uncomfortable, but
it's much better with the
blankets for sure.
I slept last night.
>> PROBST: And what's the impact
for you because you're tired or
hungry?
>> I get a little quiet.
Especially in the mornings, I'm
kind of mm...
>> PROBST: But in a social game,
withdrawing can work against
you.
>> I'm very much aware of
that.
I get the feeling I'm going home
tonight.
>> PROBST: Dolly, how are you
getting along with everybody?
>> I think I'm getting
along almost too well with
everyone and it's kind of
becoming a problem for me
because I feel kind of like
Dolly in the middle.
Four people want to vote one
way, and four people want to
vote another way, and I'm kind
of the deciding factor tonight.
>> PROBST: Eliza, are you
worried it could be you tonight?
>> I'm definitely worried
it could be me.
I mean, you never know if, you
know, somebody tells you they're
voting one way if they're
actually going to do it.
You know, you just have to pray
that people stick to their word.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Eliza, you're up.
>> My vote is for Leann
because Dolly's pretty much
running the show, but I do like
her.
>> Leann, you seem like a
great girl, just didn't have
time to get to know you.
And, um, it's purely so the five
"young'uns," as you call us, can
stick together and get through
this.
Sorry.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Leann.
Two votes Leann.
Three votes Leann.
Dolly.
One vote Dolly.
Two votes Dolly.
Three votes Leann.
Dolly.
That's three votes Dolly, three
votes Leann.
>> (softly): What?
>> PROBST: Dolly.
Four votes Dolly.
Three votes Leann.
Leann.
We're tied, four votes Leann,
four votes Dolly.
One vote left.
The second person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu...
Dolly.
Dolly, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, the person who thought
they were the swing vote is the
person you just voted out of
your tribe, so the question is:
Will tonight's vote bring you
together as a tribe or continue
to separate you?
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
>> If you were not here, we
would still have fire and
shelter and food!
>> I'll whoop that scrawny
bitch's ass, 'cause I don't
get it.
>> Do you feel I'm not
pulling my weight?
>> I saw you go on a lot of
walks.
>> I'm a grown-ass man,
and I don't take orders real
well.
>> PROBST: Both tribes will vote
out one member tonight.
Separate Tribal Councils.
Two people going home.
>> No.
>> First of all I have to
say, phew, because this game
is... is too much for me.
I wasn't cut out for this.
And I'm just a simple farm girl.
I can't plot, plan and scheme,
and I'm not too good at reading
people.
I just kind of live in my own
little world.
And I'm way too simple.
And I... I just belong on the
farm.