>> JEFF PROBST: Previously,
on Survivor:
>> Screwed you, didn't I?
>> You didn't screw me.
I'm still in the game.
You screwed Leann.
>> PROBST: While Ami felt
betrayed after her ally Leann
was voted out, Twila and Scout
felt good about what they had
done.
>> We've overthrown the queen.
I have a great mind sometimes.
I love it.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
>> No way.
>> PROBST: ...the tribe learned
that the first-place finisher
would win a new car.
>> Nice.
>> PROBST: And that the winner
and the two runners-up would
drive to the other side of the
island for a night of pampering.
Survivors ready... go!
Ami first in to dive
for her flag.
Ami led the entire race, but in
the end...
Nice job.
...Eliza came away with the car
and Ami placed second.
Chris, the third-place finisher
going on the overnight reward.
(cheering)
Eliza, Ami and Chris drove to a
luxury spot.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> And enjoyed a hot shower,
local entertainment...
>> I'm not stopping anytime
soon.
>> ...and an all-you-can-
eat gourmet dinner.
>> Listen...
>> PROBST: Ami worked strategy
on Chris and Eliza.
>> I think it would be
really smart for you guys, is to
break up Scout and Twila.
>> PROBST: But Chris wasn't
about to let Ami stay
in the game.
>> Does she think I'm stupid,
you know?
She's still working Eliza,
though.
She's strategizing.
We're pure final four and look
at our competition, a 60-year-
old woman and Twila.
I'm counting on the fact that
Eliza is mentally strong.
>> Good night, Chris.
>> PROBST: But when Ami was
alone with Eliza, the strategy
talk continued.
>> Every single time I've
had your back.
>> ELIZA: Ami has stood up for
me a lot of times.
Ami has been like a big sister
to me out here.
>> PROBST: At the Immunity
Challenge, it came down to Chris
and Ami...
Chris is on!
...but Ami couldn't come
through.
Chris wins immunity.
And Chris was safe for three
more days.
Back at camp, Eliza considered
siding with Ami and Julie to
vote out Scout.
>> Oh, she would be so mad.
I'm not afraid to change things
if I think that it's going to
get me farther in this game.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Ami confronted Twila about
swearing on her son's name and
then breaking their alliance.
>> TWILA: I am not the only
friggin' person that has lied in
this game.
You've been had.
Screw you.
>> But when you bring in
the one thing that you say is
the most sacred thing to you in
the world, to me that is not
worth a million dollars.
>> PROBST: And though Eliza
agreed with Ami about Twila's
deception...
>> Twila swore on her son,
the one thing that someone
could say to convince me.
I'm, like, "Oh, well, then
they must be true to their
word."
>> PROBST: ...she cast a vote
against her big sister.
Ami, the tribe has spoken.
Five are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
>> It's a light night out.
>> Incredibly beautiful
night.
>> After Tribal Council, we got
back to the camp and everything
was good.
Ami was gone, one less worry and
I'm the last man standing.
It seemed like it was going
to be just a quiet, you know,
easy-going night, but there was
still a lot of emotion stirring
in Twila.
The fact that Eliza had brought
up Twila swearing on her son's
name.
>> Sorry, T.
>> You don't know how bad
I feel about saying that, and
then you just keep rubbing salt
in the wound, which is fine.
>> You know what...
>> But the only one I want to
worry about it with is my son,
when I go home.
>> We're all dropping it,
completely, and I'm sorry
I brought it up.
>> Because I am, you
know, I'm sorry I ever
said it.
I am so sorry that I ever made
that statement.
I am tired of it.
I'm tired of hearing about it,
period.
The only one that I've got to
condole with or say anything to
is my son when I get home.
The rest of you mother ... can
kiss my ... period.
>> Yeah, we're past it
and we're over it.
>> Yeah, everybody's over it.
>> I think that's a little
uncalled for.
>> I was apologizing.
I was apologizing.
There's no need to...
>> I think it's a lot
called for, Julie.
>> Why?
>> You all keep ... dogging me
about this ... and I'm sick of
it.
>> Your son?
>> So let it go.
>> I haven't... your son?
>> Yes.
>> I haven't brought up
your son once.
>> Oh, ...
>> Twila's outburst really
looked like a heinous
insecurity just projected on us.
And I'm actually kind of glad
she did it, 'cause I know it
completely turned everybody off
and I'm going to use it against
her later on.
That was so uncalled for.
>> That was so...
I was apologizing for
bringing up something that she
didn't want me to bring up.
>> You know what?
>> And she was like,
"Mother... go to hell."
I'm like, "Oh, my God."
>> I know.
>> It's shocking.
Nobody speaks to me like that.
Nobody speaks to me like that,
and I don't...
I don't tolerate it.
I guess Twila got a little upset
at Tribal Council, but she got
even more upset when we got
back and she was cursing at me.
Yes, I brought up the fact that
she swore on her son to both me
and somebody else, and one of
those times it was a lie, so it
made me wary of the fact that
she had sworn on her son to me.
You know, she's the one who did
it.
If you can't live with your past
actions, you shouldn't have done
it.
(thumping)
>> Good morning.
>> Against herself,
towards us, more so towards you.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I knew that it wasn't
a good thing what Twila was
doing.
She definitely offended Julie.
She definitely offended Eliza.
Eliza being part of this four-
person alliance with Scout,
Twila and myself, you know, it's
important to try to keep a
level, you know, understanding.
She's taken a road she doesn't
need to take.
It's dangerous for her position
in the game.
>> Why would it be a big
deal to vote Twila off instead
of me?
>> I don't know.
>> Just from your perspective,
your position.
>> I don't know.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't think it would.
I would definitely consider
making a deal with Julie.
Sometimes when it's in your best
interest to abandon an alliance,
you have to do that to get
yourself further in the game.
>> Right.
I mean, Chris is like either/or,
'cause he could win against me.
And if anything, Twila's his
semi-competition, and I'll talk
to him about it.
>> Just say, "Oh, I mentioned
it to Eliza and I told her I
was going to talk to you."
Don't say...
>> I'm not gonna... yeah,
I'm not saying you're agreeing.
All day I've been shuffling my
ideas and my plan to Eliza.
I've been playing up the fact
that we want to get rid
of Twila.
But her only dilemma is that she
is going to be faithful to Chris
and if Chris doesn't buy it,
then there's no point.
So I have to approach Chris in
an appropriate time and manner.
You know, it's all benching on
that for me.
It could either continue my game
or end it abruptly.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Okay.
Today's reward challenge will
give you a second chance with
some challenges you have tackled
in the past.
All five of you will go through
the mud pit.
The first four to get to the
other side move on to the
next round.
Those four will tackle the
pigpen, where you must get
inside the pigpen, get a pig and
get that pig in its cage.
The first three to do this move
on to the next round, where you
must put together a Tiki puzzle.
The first two to correctly solve
the Tiki puzzle move to the
final round.
The last two will race up and
across a balance beam, down the
other side where, using a
slingshot, you must break three
tiles.
You'll raise a torch, torch will
light the wok, you win reward.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For the winner, you
will take a horseback ride.
>> Ooh!
>> My favorite.
>> PROBST: And you will end up
at Mount Yasur, one of the most
active volcanoes in the world.
Of course, you'll have a little
snack fitting for volcano
viewing: hot dogs.
>> Oh, my God, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Wine and/or hot
chocolate and beer.
You'll spend the night at Mount
Yasur.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: All right.
We're going to draw numbers for
position.
We'll get started.
First four through the mud pit
move on to the next round.
Survivors, ready.
Go!
Chris, Twila, Eliza with a
slight lead and then Julie and
then Scout.
Twila and Eliza.
Chris bringing it on.
Julie struggling, but she's
still ahead of Scout.
First four across, Chris is
across, Eliza is across, Twila
is across and Julie moving on to
the next round.
Scout is the first one
eliminated.
Here we go, the first three to
catch a pig that has an orange
stripe and get that pig in its
cage moves on to the next round.
Survivors ready.
Go!
(pigs squealing)
Chris has one.
(squealing)
Julie and Eliza fighting for
one.
Eliza had it and she lost it.
Julie has one.
Chris is in.
>> Go, Twila.
Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Julie is moving on.
And Twila moving on to the
next round.
>> Nice try, honey.
>> PROBST: Eliza's out.
First two to correctly get their
Tiki put together move on.
Survivors, ready.
Go!
Got to untie knots, take the
puzzle apart and then put it
back together again.
Chris and Twila wasting no time.
Julie going to untie all her
knots first.
Julie has all the knots undone.
Chris has all his pieces off,
Julie right behind...
Twila right behind.
Chris is going to do his on the
ground.
First two move on.
>> I think I got it.
>> PROBST: That's not right.
Two people are moving on to the
final.
>> Please say yes.
>> PROBST: Twila's right.
She's moving on.
>> Yes, whoo!
>> Way to go, Twila!
>> PROBST: Chris, trying to
figure out where he's
gone wrong.
Julie's right, moving on.
Julie and Twila in the final.
Chris, one piece over there you
never used.
This piece right here.
>> No, I didn't see that.
>> PROBST: Final two, Twila and
Julie, for a horseback ride to
Mount Yasur.
Survivors, ready.
Go!
Twila trips on the ladder, Julie
with a little bit of a lead.
Got to get across this
balance beam.
Julie is first over.
Twila still doing well on the
beam.
Time to catch up.
Julie untying her slingshot.
Twila took a big fall on the
net, she's hurt.
Julie untying the slingshot.
Twila making short order
of the knot.
Twila starting to catch up.
Julie has her slingshot, got to
break three plates, releasing
them from the wires.
Julie is going to get the first
shot in.
Twila right behind.
Julie, with one shot, breaks her
first plate.
>> Way to go, Julie.
>> PROBST: Julie lines up for
her second shot.
Julie breaks her second plate.
Twila breaks her first plate.
>> I'm winning this.
>> PROBST: Julie says she's
going to win it.
She's got one plate left...
and she does.
(scattered cheers)
Julie going to Mount Yasur.
>> Way to go, Julie.
>> PROBST: All right, Julie,
nice effort.
You're going to Mount Yasur--
horseback ride, hot dogs, beer.
Who you taking with you?
>> Well, it's ironic, 'cause
none of these people would've
taken me, so I'm gonna
take Chris.
(groans): Oh... brother.
>> PROBST: All right.
You three, nice effort.
Heading back to camp muddy.
Head on out.
>> Julie won the reward.
And she picked me, and we
cleaned up after the muddy
challenge we went through.
And we journeyed through the
jungle and we finally come out
into this extremely ashy, dense
area.
>> Wow.
>> Lord, that thing is mammoth.
>> The decision to bring
Chris-- I knew none of them were
going to bring me-- but Chris I
had the funnest with, I needed
to talk to, and he's my door to
open to get me further in this
game, so it only made sense to
bring Chris.
>> Hello.
>> Hello, hello.
>> Julie.
>> Joe? Okay.
>> Okay, Joe.
>> Let's go.
Let's take a walk up there.
>> Okay, let's go.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Oh, Chris, can you
believe it?
>> This is beautiful.
>> Wow. Wow.
Whoa.
Hope you make it.
>> He's awful nervous.
>> There was one part
when we were crossing the river,
okay, and Chris is in the river
just looking around.
And he just looked so hopeless
out there, I just couldn't
help but laugh.
>> He's not wanting to go
nowhere.
>> Yeah? Just give a kick.
Kick on the side.
(clicking tongue)
>> Kick him?
>> Kick, yeah.
Stronger.
>> This horse and me had
trouble getting to know each
other at first, you know?
It took us a while to, you know,
build a trusting relationship.
Go.
Whoa!
So, okay, well, off to a little
bit of a rough start on the
horse, but everything else went
great.
This is beautiful.
>> Isn't it?
>> We walked down this
long trail, and it was awesome
just looking at everything on
our way up.
>> Finally, we come around
the far side of Mount Yasur.
>> Here we are.
This is your hut for the night.
>> Ow!
Oh, my God!
I see foot-long hot dogs, huge
rolls, onions and relish, wine,
beer.
We are thrilled, so we're like,
"Okay, what can we do?
Let's get going."
>> Guys...
>> Yeah.
Joe comes back and he's, like,
"Bring the hot dogs.
We're going to heat them
in the vent."
You look around, there's all
these steam vents coming up.
It was probably about ten feet
away.
>> This is nice and warm.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Nice and hot, see?
>> Is it hot enough it'll
cook this?
>> Yes. Sure.
>> Great little oven.
>> Oh! I'm sorry.
That is hot.
>> Yeah.
We go over to the vent,
and put some corn in the bottom,
and just stick them in.
Three minutes later,
they're ready.
>> Okay...
Oh, yeah, look at that.
>> You think?
>> Yeah. Take a bite.
Mine's cooked.
>> We'll leave the corns for...
>> God, oh, my God.
So we doll up our rolls and we
ate just four hot dogs nonstop,
foot-long, great, yum.
I was in heaven.
Oh, my God, Chris.
>> You know, Julie won
the reward.
It didn't surprise me that she
picked me.
She wants to go further in the
game, and she knows that her
name is coming up for
elimination.
>> Are you a lot tighter
with Twila than I thought
you were?
>> Um... no, I've never
been real tight with Twila.
>> Right. So who do you
feel most loyal to?
>> Since the merge, you.
You've never done nothing...
you've done nothing but help me
since then.
I see that.
I know that.
Me and Julie got a little bit
of, you know, a bond between us,
you know.
She let me know that she doesn't
want to leave.
She wants to stay in the game.
>> Eliza's like, "I'm
aligned with everyone, but Chris
is the only one... if you talk
to him then I'll consider."
She's like, "I'll go along with
it if Chris goes along with it."
>> Well, that's because
she told me I'm the only one
she trusts now.
>> Right.
>> I don't know, Julie worked
it pretty good.
There's nothing that Julie or
Eliza would like more than for
me to jump on their side and
vote off Twila.
And I didn't tell her no.
I'm the last guy standing.
I sit and I think, "Is this a
bad thing or a good thing?"
I just haven't decided yet.
Sure, I mean, I know darn well
you could influence Eliza.
>> Yeah.
>> Without a doubt.
And, yeah, the three of us could
completely turn the game around.
>> Chris was very open-minded
and he's open to help me
progress in the game, so Chris
is my rock right now.
>> Get them bananas over
here and just start cutting
some of them up and put them in
a soup just so they don't
go to waste.
>> You want to bury the
other ones?
>> The big ones?
>> Yeah. Where are they?
>> Did I unbury them or
do you want to bury the
rest of them?
>> No, did you unbury?
>> Nope, I didn't.
>> Where are they?
>> I'm not telling.
>> T...?
>> If you ask me one more
time, I'm going to let the damn
things rot in the ground.
>> Twila has been telling
us that she hid these bananas.
She buried them in order to help
them ripen and won't tell us
where they are.
>> Are you hungry for a
banana, little one?
>> I'm over the fact that
she's saying, "Oh, we're going
to let them rot in the ground."
It's so patronizing.
>> You're acting like a
kid, though. Get over it.
>> Why are you being so
childish about the damn bananas?
>> She don't want you to
have the bananas yet, honey.
>> Wearing me slick.
>> She's saving those
bananas so we all have something
to eat at breakfast each
morning.
>> I'll just go bury the
rest of them and then let you
know if I decide I want to tell
you where they are.
>> Okay.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Touché.
She got you.
She got you, Twila.
(laughing)
>> For Scout, for Twila,
for me, it's just gotten to the
point where we cannot hold back
anymore and especially Twila.
She's just so childish and
immature and so obnoxious and
annoying, and I hate the way
she treats me.
I hate...
I mean, oh, my God.
>> It just don't make no
sense why she's being so
freakin' childish over it.
I don't care.
They can stay in the ground and
rot, I ain't digging 'em up now.
It's her way or no way.
Forget that.
>> I'm so sick of Twila.
I just want her to go home now.
>> Full moon, Chris.
>> Awesome.
>> It's like a challenge
all over again.
>> No kidding.
>> It's going to be great.
I like watching this.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Do you see?
>> Yeah, that is awesome.
So Joe comes back and, you know,
we're like, okay.
He goes, "Look, I'm going to
take you up here."
So we all three took off up this
little trail up the volcano.
Watch the rocks.
>> Oh, my God, Chris.
>> Oh...
>> Oh, my God.
Do you believe it?
>> This is where we're
going to sit and watch.
>> No way.
Julie, do you see how close we
are now?
>> I know.
Oh, my God.
Gosh.
>> No way.
>> Oh, my...
>> It's like a time bomb.
>> It is.
This is definitely like
fireworks.
>> It was amazing because
every time the volcano erupted,
the volcanic rock would shoot
out and it just glowed.
It was like the Fourth of July.
Oh, granny, give us a big one.
>> Oh...
I saw a volcano exploding the
whole night.
It was one of the most beautiful
things I've ever witnessed.
>> There is absolutely no
other experience in my life I
can compare it to.
>> Wow.
>> I don't know if I'll
ever have another experience
like it.
I mean, how often do you get to
sit at the mouth of a volcano
and watch it explode?
Is it talking to us or what?
>> It's saying good-bye.
>> Got me scared.
I had to turn around.
>> Just about home.
>> Oh, I see Chris and
Jules coming.
(animal call)
>> Coming, slowpoke?
>> I just filled your
water jug, J.B.
I don't know where yours is
or I'd fill it for you.
>> I knew that.
I'm glad, yeah.
>> Where's Twila?
How is her foot?
I've been thinking about her.
After the reward this morning,
we come back to camp.
Right away, you know, Scout
hugged me and she's thinking the
same thing I'm thinking.
It's game time.
I just let her know nothing has
changed.
We're all four together and
then, you know, Twila.
She's a basket case.
You've got to reassure her.
>> Coming back to camp
was perfect.
Everything fell together.
Everyone's thinking on the same
terms, keeping an eye on things.
That's what I got to do.
>> Come sit and talk to
me for a minute.
I was thrilled to get Julie and
Chris back because presumably
Julie has spoken to Chris about
voting for Twila.
And if Chris is going to go for
it, then I might go for it also.
>> Everything is good.
Julie picked me for strategy.
She's worried about her spot
in the game.
She knows that us four have
an alliance.
>> Right, right.
So if any one of the four of us
wins immunity, we're voting
Julie off.
>> I don't know.
Depends on, you know, our best
interest in the game and how far
we can go.
I think without a doubt Twila is
gonna stick with Scout, Scout is
gonna stick with Twila.
>> Oh, yeah, definitely.
>> That-that worries me
a little bit.
>> But if Julie stays in
the game, we're automatically in
the final three.
>> I'm open-minded to
exactly what you said, because,
you know, me and Julie have
talked and we had discussed
us three...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...as being better for
all three of us.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yeah.
I sat down with Eliza on the
beach.
We went over a scenario about
me, her and Julie taking
out Twila.
I mean, I don't trust Scout.
I don't trust Twila.
I don't trust Eliza.
I don't trust Julie, and
they don't trust each other.
And the most screwed-up thing
about it is, I think they all
trust me.
So... it's... it's getting
really crazy.
I've probably made it this way
myself because I am playing
both sides.
Everything's good.
We'll just have to see how this
immunity challenge goes, and,
you know, if it falls in the
right direction, we'll talk and
do what's best for us...
to the final three.
>> Oh, yeah.
To the final two.
>> Well, yeah, I mean, right.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Go ahead and have
a seat, guys.
Ready for today's Immunity
Challenge?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Chris.
Give it up.
Immunity back up for grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
I'm gonna tell you a story about
a legendary man in these parts,
and then you're gonna have to
answer a series of questions.
Ready for the story?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, back in
the 1200s, this guy Chief Roy
Mata comes to this land,
conquers it.
His first goal was to bring
peace by uniting all of the
tribes, and he accomplished
that.
But sadly, the peace didn't
last very long.
15 years later, Roy Mata was
murdered, not by an enemy or a
rival chief, but by his own
brother.
Now, it certainly wasn't
forbidden to bury a chief on the
land that he ruled, but the
locals were so afraid of the
power of the spirit of Roy Mata
that they took the body to a
remote location and they buried
him there with his 18 assistant
chiefs, their wives and all of
Roy Mata's wives.
Before being buried alive, the
men were given a strong brew of
kava, not because it was
customary but because it put
them in a dream-like relaxed
state.
The women, however, were
strangled to death before being
buried.
Once the ceremony was complete,
the land was declared taboo, and
nobody visited for seven
centuries.
One footnote, the name Roy Mata,
not a popular name today.
In fact, it has never been used
since.
That is your story.
Your challenge now to see how
much of that information you've
retained.
Here's how it'll work.
There are six huts scattered in
the jungle.
You'll race to a hut where
you'll find a puzzle.
Put the puzzle together, which
has the question, read it and
then choose between answer A or
answer B.
Attached to each answer is a bag
full of tusks.
Without looking, reach in and
pull one out.
If you're wrong, you will grab a
black tusk, in which case you
have to race back to the center,
toss it in the urn and return to
the hut to answer the question
correctly.
If you're right, you'll grab a
white tusk, bring that back to
your post, put it on your
necklace.
There are six huts.
First person to get five answers
correctly wins immunity.
Ready to do this?
>> Let's roll.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
For immunity and a guaranteed
spot in the final four.
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> Okay. "When Roy Mata
conquered the land, what was his
first goal?"
"Unite the tribes."
>> PROBST: Eliza heads back
first.
She's got one right.
>> "The body of Roy Mata
was not buried on his
homeland..."
Because...
"It was forbidden by custom."
"Locals feared his spirit."
>> PROBST: Chris back.
He's got one right.
>> "Roy Mata was poisoned
by..."
"A family..."
>> PROBST: Here's Julie.
She's got one right.
Eliza, Chris, Julie with
one right.
>> "Before being buried
alive, the men drank kava
because..."
"It was customary."
>> PROBST: Twila has her first
one right.
>> "The wives of the assistant
chiefs serving under Roy Mata
were also buried alive."
>> PROBST: Scout got it wrong,
throws it in the urn.
>> "To this date, the
name Roy Mata is..."
"Never used." "A popular name."
"Never used."
>> PROBST: Eliza heading back
with her second question.
Eliza in the lead with two.
Here's Julie back with another
one.
Chris back with his second one.
Eliza extends her lead.
Back with her third correct
answer.
Julie racing back.
She's got her third.
Looking for an opening hut.
Chris trying to get in this.
Eliza with three, Julie with
three, Chris with two.
Eliza got her fourth one right.
Julie right behind her.
She has her fourth one.
We're dead even.
Between Eliza and Julie.
Julie waiting on a spot
from Twila.
Eliza with four, Julie
with four.
First one back with the white
tusk wins immunity, guaranteed
spot in the final four.
>> "Before being buried
alive, the men drank kava
because..."
"It relaxed them."
"It was customary."
>> PROBST: Here comes Eliza,
number five, and with that,
Eliza wins immunity!
All right, Eliza.
Get over here.
>> My first time.
>> PROBST: Well, it's a good
time to be the first time.
So the other four of you, after
36 days of making it this far,
tonight the game will end for
one of you.
I'll see you tonight at Tribal
Council.
Head on back to camp.
(indistinct conversation)
>> For the first time, I
won individual immunity today,
and I am guaranteed a spot in
the final four.
It's awesome.
It's a great feeling.
I'd like to win every immunity
challenge from here on out.
This is gonna be the first
Tribal Council I haven't brought
my bag to.
I think that tonight Chris,
Julie and I are going to shock
the hell out of everyone and
vote off Twila, and it's just...
it's a really exciting prospect.
Chris has proved me right so
far, and I just hope he
continues to do so.
>> (indistinct talking)
>> Yeah. Not a big deal.
>> What are they talking
about?
>> I don't know.
>> Putting a lot of trust
in Chris, you know?
He could guarantee himself a
final-three spot with them.
>> But... I don't think
he'll do that.
>> We're three, they're
two.
That's it.
Case closed, right, Scout?
>> Right, absolutely.
>> Nothing stops us.
>> If I'm going home,
you'd better tell me.
>> You guys...
I'm here because of you guys.
It's not changing.
I mean, don't even doubt it.
I would tell you, you got it?
We're going all the way, to the
final three.
>> Okay.
>> Scout and Twila are
definitely convinced that
Julie's the next to go.
And then there's me.
I'm still weighing my options,
but I'm going back and forth
like a teeter-totter, you know?
I'm thinking, one moment I think
I'm gonna keep Julie around, and
the next moment, you know, I'm
thinking maybe I better stick
with Twila and Scout.
Now, just listen to me.
It's just a question.
It's not what's gonna happen
necessarily.
If I decide to vote Julie off
tonight because I think it's
best for me and you, that
doesn't affect me and your pact,
right?
>> The only thing is, you
know Scout and Twila are not
gonna go against each other.
That means whichever one of us
doesn't win immunity is going up
against one of them, whichever
one we decide to vote off first,
in a challenge at Tribal
Council.
>> I know.
>> That's what that means.
And so yes, it doesn't affect
our pact, but that means that
one of the two of us could end
up in the final three with two
of them, meaning 100% we do not
end up in the final two.
>> I know, I know.
>> What's up?
>> I don't know, you tell me.
What's up, Eliza?
>> I don't know.
I just feel like you're ...
with me.
>> You got immunity.
>> You're right, I do
have immunity tonight, but if I
don't have immunity tomorrow
night, then who's gone, T?
I think you're a liar, T.
>> Who else has been lying?
Are you in this alliance with us
to the end?
>> I hadn't told a lie in
this game.
>> And have you been
talking to Julie about anything,
or is that just... that's okay
for you to do?
You said, swore to us that you
was in this final-four alliance
till the end, so what've you
been talking to Julie about?
>> Hey, I'm gonna listen
to her.
>> And you're not saying,
"Okay, we would like to do this
and this and get Twila and Scout
out of here" or anything?
>> I'm listening.
I'm listening, and you know
what?
>> And you ain't said a word?
>> I would consider it,
because you've been trying to
plot against me since day one.
>> You've been on the
edge for the last three
friggin'
days.
You're driving everybody
friggin' nuts.
Chill out.
You got one night that you know
you ain't going nowhere.
Enjoy it.
>> I will.
>> Now, Chris, what are
you thinking?
>> (laughs): What?
I'm just laying here, you know,
in the hammock.
>> No, you was talking to...
I just come up.
I was just kind of listening to
what was being said.
>> I'm hearing Eliza out.
She's talking to me.
>> Okay.
>> Everybody's scrambling.
I just think I'm in a better
position than, you know, Twila,
Scout, Eliza, or Julie right now
because I'm-I'm, I'm pretty much
the middle man, as far as I
know.
You know, what them four have
conspired or talked about, I
don't know.
I don't trust any of them.
They're thick as thieves, man.
They're all women.
How do you trust any of them?
So, I don't know what I'm going
to do.
I'm messing with both sides, but
it's kind of easy to do right
now.
I need to do it to figure out
what my best option is right
now.
It's probably in my best
interest to go with you and
Eliza because Scout and Twila
are too thick.
I haven't broke my word that
often in this game and I thought
I would be a cutthroat piece
of...
>> But isn't she easier
to do that to than me?
>> What I'm comparing
this to is my friendship with
you compared to my friendship
with Twila.
>> Right.
>> And my friendship with
you is a hell of a lot more than
my-- I mean, come on.
We've joked around, and, you
know, I call you my little
sister.
It's just... it's totally
different.
We'll keep you.
We're gonna vote off Twila.
>> Chris approaches me.
He says he's gonna straight-out
vote for Twila, basically saying
that our friendship is weighing
on his decision tonight.
I hope he keeps me around.
That's all I can do.
I don't know for sure.
I'm not going to be extremely
paranoid.
I'm just really gonna be even
keel and hope that it goes in my
favor.
>> I haven't liked the
game since we merged.
>> We have no reason to
be stressed.
I've made my decision.
It's not gonna change.
It's me, you, and Scout voting
for Julie, and that's it.
That's not gonna change.
I'm not even hesitating.
Me and Julie's become friends.
I'm sending her home tonight.
>> Chris has guaranteed
me that I'm not going home
tonight.
Part of me wants to believe
Chris wholeheartedly, but-- it's
a game.
I just cannot do it.
I cannot let my guard down.
You can't trust nobody now.
Nobody.
You're playing for a million
dollars.
People have murdered for
less than a million dollars,
you know?
Come on.
>> I'm excited to have immunity.
>> I know, you ought to be.
>> I told Julie that I'm
keeping her.
I told Twila that I'm keeping
her.
I'm gonna put myself in the best
possible situation to win the
game.
It's tough right now.
I'm gonna have to make a
decision before long.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury: Sarge,
Chad, Leanne, and Ami-- voted
out at the last Tribal Council.
Welcome to Tribal Council.
Well, let talk about 36 days, a
lot of wear and tear, physically
and certainly emotionally.
Everybody here wants to win the
game.
Have you guys started thinking
about who deserves to win this
game?
Twila, is there any way that
somebody could be unworthy of
winning?
>> I don't know.
>> Be honest.
>> PROBST: You don't know or you
don't want to say?
>> You are being hard on
me, you know that?
>> PROBST: Am I?
>> Yes, sir, you are.
>> PROBST: Are you saying there
are people here tonight that
absolutely do not deserve to be
in the final five.
>> Just tell him what you
feel, Twila.
>> Yeah, come on.
>> Why hold back now?
>> My personal opinion is
yes, there is.
>> It's me, by the way,
in case anybody was wondering.
>> PROBST: Well, Twila, it's no
secret you and Eliza have not
gotten along for a long time.
>> No. No, there's no secret.
>> PROBST: Eliza, anybody here
that doesn't deserve to be here.
>> Even though they would
say the opposite of me, I think
all the people sitting here
deserve to be here.
That doesn't mean that I like
them.
That doesn't mean that I don't
like other people, who are no
longer in the game, a million
times more than I like some of
the people sitting here next to
me, but I think we all deserve
to be here.
We wouldn't be here otherwise.
>> PROBST: What about you,
Julie?
At this point, when you have to
vote, obviously, it's strategic,
but is there any part of you
starting to whittle things down,
thinking who I want to go to the
final four with are these people
and this is why?
>> Um... I guess, just
judging people.
The longer you're with them, you
see their antics and tactics and
I feel like I can, I know who I
can trust and who I can't trust
and who cares about me or who
doesn't care about me.
>> PROBST: At this point, do you
think any of these other four
care about you?
>> Yeah, I know that some do.
>> PROBST: Chris, what's tough
for you about tonight's vote?
>> Toughest vote yet.
>> PROBST: For you?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Why?
>> Uh... kind of caught
in the middle.
It's a vote I don't even want to
cast, but I, you know, I've got
to play the game.
>> PROBST: All right.
Eliza, you have immunity.
As always, you can keep it or
assign it to somebody else.
>> I think I better hold
on to it, Jeff.
>> Oh, give it to Twila.
>> It's my first time.
>> PROBST: Okay, you cannot vote
for Eliza.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Scout, you're up.
>> Jules, a wise woman once
gave me some good information:
"Go back to your roots, Jules.
Rediscover your roots."
>> Twila, I have been
waiting to vote you off since
the day I met you.
I cannot believe that 36 days
later, I'm finally getting
this opportunity.
>> It's tough, but I
gotta play the game.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote... Julie.
Twila.
One vote Julie, one vote Twila.
Julie.
Two votes Julie, one vote Twila.
Twila.
Two votes Twila, two votes
Julie.
I'll read the last vote.
The 14th person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu...
Julie.
You need to bring me your torch.
Julie, the tribe has spoken.
Well, you have made it to the
final four.
Over the next three days, there
will be three Tribal Councils,
two immunity challenges, one
winner.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I don't think you
deserve to be here, Eliza.
You have done nothing but boil
freakin' water.
>> I think Twila's a dumb bitch.
>> PROBST: The heat is on.
>> I hope they kill each other.
>> PROBST: Only three days are
left.
Next time, in a two-hour
special, find out who will
become the sole survivor.
>> It's for a million bucks.
That'll change your life.
>> Here I am.
It's day 36, I'm done.
Little bit of a surprise.
You know, I-I thought Chris and
I had this kind of
straightforward brother-sister
kind of slap-each-other-around
relationship, and Chris was kind
of my crutch today and he told
me 100% that he was gonna vote
for Twila.
I don't know if he changed the
last minute.
I'm curious.