>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> Y'all need to leave me
alone right now.
>> PROBST: Feeling desperate,
Rory played the anger card.
>> You guys are so smoked
in that you don't even see
honesty when it comes right at
y'all.
The ladies made a mistake in
telling me that I would've been
eliminated before Bubba was.
I'm going to play it up.
>> What are you thinking?
>> PROBST: At Lopevi, Julie and
Twila considered their
situation at the new tribe.
>> There's no doubt about it.
We are...
Julie and I are...
Being the only two women over
here, we're both vulnerable.
We know it.
>> Is it that a pig?
>> PROBST: When tree mail
arrived, Rory gathered the women
and put it all on the line.
>> My apologies to all of
you for the horrible, horrible
things that I said last night,
but I will not continue to slave
around camp if I do not have a
shot at making it through Tribal
Council.
There's no way in hell these
ladies bought any of that.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the tribes played for
steak and eggs.
Go!
In a muddy race to gather pigs,
Lopevi took a commanding lead.
>> Eliza trying.
She can't do it.
When Eliza let her tribe down...
Lopevi wins reward!
Back at camp...
>> Anybody want Cajun spice
on their steak?
>> PROBST: ...Lopevi savored
their victory.
>> This is better than sex
right now.
Oh, damn!
>> PROBST: While at Yasur, Eliza
took the loss hard...
>> I'm not used to being
bad at things.
>> PROBST: ...opening the door
for Rory.
>> I think I just found my
little tiny crack.
Settling into their new Lopevi
tribe...
>> I'd like to tan my ....
>> PROBST: ...Julie worked her
best assets while Twila plotted
with Sarge.
>> Lea is someone that
knows what it means to give your
word.
I said, "Twila, you got my word
as a man, you are in the four to
the end."
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, it was Leann who cost
Yasur the victory.
Leann getting a second wind, but
it's not enough.
Lopevi wins immunity!
And Lopevi won their fourth
challenge in a row.
Before Tribal Council, Lisa
offended Ami.
>> Do you want me to go get
more manioc?
>> Whoa, in case what?
Lisa said, oh, she wanted to
know where the manioc was just
in case I wasn't around.
Oops.
Did that really just come
out your mouth?
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Ami's distrust for Lisa caused
the female alliance to crumble,
and Lisa was voted out of the
tribe.
Lisa, the tribe has spoken.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> The camp's running really
well.
I mean, everyone kind of has
just fallen into some work
roles, and, uh, most of us do
several things.
Everybody's getting water, doing
the dishes.
There's one person that's not
doing his share, and that's
John.
>> I feel fine today.
I'm tired and bored.
For the most part, there's
really not much to do around
here, so we just kind of kick
back and relax.
>> John is an enigma.
I wanted to ask him today, "How
can you sit there and look
around at us while everyone else
is working?"
It's beyond me, but he just does
it.
He's gotten away with it to this
point, but now we're starting to
make comments.
>> He grubs the food.
>> Yeah, he does.
>> He'll eat three or four
bowls.
>> I know.
>> Well, I could eat
three or four bowls, you know.
I'd make sure everybody else is
getting the same amount, but I'd
eat more.
>> I think he realizes
he's doing it, too.
It's like, "Oh, man, that
was..." I don't want to judge
the dude, but...
>> He's the kind of person that
coasts through the game.
>> Yeah.
>> That's exactly what he is.
>> He is.
>> And he's not coasting
through this game with us in it.
>> No, no way.
>> When I, uh, wake up in
the morning, usually the first
thing that I do is I bow down
and I pray, and today in
particular, I got a lot of
things to be thankful for,
because for some twist in fate,
I cracked these ladies, and they
carried me through one more
night.
So this morning, I was
particularly thankful, and I
might not be able to bounce
around laughing and smiling, but
I'm just so thankful.
Then it's down to business.
So my new objective is to work
on Leann and Ami and wrap myself
into their relationship, 'cause
I'm still an alliance of one
right now.
Well, Ami, here's my situation.
I need to know where you guys
stand with regard to me, because
there's no way in hell I want to
be eliminated before Eliza.
I had explained to you that I
would back you all the way
through jury and everything
else.
>> The biggest thing... the
biggest thing for all the women
was no women's alliance has
stayed together through this
game ever, not once, ever.
That's kind of what's keeping us
going is that we want women...
>> Then what I'm going to
tell you this.
You know, if-if I get smoked,
how far are you guys going to
go, you know?
And for me, just on a personal
level, I mean, give me a break.
Eliza over me?
How much can she bring to this
team, and how much have I
already brought to the table?
>> Unfortunately for you,
the fact that the women had this
alliance excludes you right off
the bat.
>> Well, you know...
>> What happens when the
merger comes with the men?
>> ( sighs )
>> How do you keep your
face and-and say, "You know
what?
I'm sticking with the women?"
And what about the guys back
home?
>> You... What do you mean?
What do you...
what do you...?
What-what...?
What do you mean, what about
the guys back home?
>> Don't cuss at me.
>> What do you mean?
>> Well, don't cuss at me.
>> Then don't treat me like I'm
some sort of lackey.
What you want is your playing
me, and you want me to continue
doing all the work, and 110%...
>> I don't want you to do
anything.
>> Rory...
>> Sit and your butt and
have a good time with it, Rory.
>> Rory, we're not
playing it off...
>> I've already told you,
just like I told you on the
trail yesterday, that I would
support you 120%.
I don't give a ...
about Sarge.
I don't give a ... about Chad.
I don't know them men.
Who has been pumping this whole
time?
>> Me, you.
>> Right.
>> Yeah.
Leann.
>> Right.
>> Yeah.
>> And you can't say that
about everybody on Yasur.
The ladies of Yasur have
basically told me that I'm going
to be the next one voted out.
That's done a job on my head, so
I've decided that I will go into
self-destruct mode, and one of
the things that I discussed with
my wife before I came out here
was I am going to institute a
slash, burn and salt the earth
policy.
What that means is if I get
voted off this island, the Yasur
tribe will burn.
I can guarantee that.
>> PROBST: What's going on,
guys?OBST: What's going on,
>> Hey, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Getting your first
look at the new Yasur tribe.
>> Lisa.
Lisa is gone.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Lisa voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
>> Not what we said.
Not what we said.
>> PROBST: Lopevi, a lot of
surprised looks on your faces as
you saw that it was Lisa voted
out.
>> Yeah, big time.
>> Yeah, I thought for
sure that they would get rid of
him, keep the women together.
>> Wow, what can I say?
>> PROBST: Okay.
Let's get to today's challenge.
It is for reward, and it will
require a steady hand.
On my go, one tribe member at a
time is going to begin breaking
coconuts.
Once you've filled your coconut
shell, you'll make your way
through the obstacle course.
For the first stage, you got to
make your way through a wood
crawl.
Second stage, you'll go up and
over a see-saw.
The third stage, you will high
step through a series of wooden
hurdles.
Fourth stage: another see-saw,
and the final stage, you'll
crawl through the bamboo cage.
When you reach the end, you'll
pour the juice remaining in your
coconut shell into a hand-blown
glass jar.
The jars are not identical, but
the black lines designate an
equal amount.
If you spill all of your juice
while you're on the obstacle
course, you come back and you go
to the back of the line.
First tribe to get back to the
start with their glass container
filled with coconut juice wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: You're playing for a
visit to a home café.
We have a coffee maker, lots of
Folgers coffee-- every flavor
you could think of-- something
for everybody.
We also have croissants.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: We also have juices.
And because it is a home café,
also a little reminder of the
love that is waiting for you
back home.
>> Oh, come on.
>> PROBST: And there's one more
thing.
The winning tribe will take a
coffee-maker, mugs and coffee
back to their camp with them.
>> Yeah!
>> Oh...
my God.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: Okay, Lopevi, you
have one extra member.
You're sitting somebody out.
Who's it going to be?
>> Sarge.
>> PROBST: Sarge, you'll take a
spot on the bench.
Everybody else, wait for my go.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
For reward-- a visit to the Home
Café.
Survivors ready.
Go!
John has his cracked, so does
Eliza filling up her coconut
shell.
John filling up his ball.
Eliza first on the course.
John on the course.
Both in the first obstacle.
Taking care of that juice.
Every drop counts.
Eliza on the seesaw, John
falling behind.
>> Nice job, Eliza.
>> Good girl, good girl.
>> Come on, John.
>> PROBST: Eliza high-steps
through the hurdles.
John does a good job on the
seesaw.
Quickly through the hurdles.
John catching up.
( wood thudding )
Eliza into the final leg.
Coffee, croissants, juice, a
little love from home at stake.
Quite a bit.
Nice job.
Back to the start.
>> Good job, Eliza.
>> Nice job, Eliza.
>> Oh, yeah, right there.
>> Superstar.
>> Way to go, way to go,
way to go.
>> Come on, John.
>> That's it.
>> Come on over, buddy up.
Come on, let's go.
>> PROBST: John, quite a bit of
juice, too.
Back to the start.
Chad on the course.
Got a lot of ground to make up.
Stretching to get their body
through there.
>> Nice move.
>> Doing great, Chad.
>> Good job, Chad.
>> Doing good, doing
good.
>> Good job.
>> Way to go, way to go,
Leann.
>> PROBST: Chad doing a great
job on the seesaw.
He's halfway.
>> It's all you, Chad.
>> PROBST: Chad through both
seesaws.
He's into the final leg of the
obstacle, making up time on
Leann.
>> Keep it up.
Almost there.
Good job, babe.
>> PROBST: Leann again fighting
those long limbs.
And Chad passes Leann, and he is
through the bamboo cage.
>> Come on, Chad, great
job.
>> PROBST: Yasur and Lopevi both
on the course.
Chris with a very full coconut
shell.
How much of it will make it to
the end?
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: Scout deliberately
dumps her juice.
New strategy.
She's going to go to the end of
the line, let the fast ones run
the course.
>> Go, girl.
>> Good job, Julie.
>> Yeah!
>> Nice.
>> PROBST: Julie with more for
Lopevi.
Yasur getting closer.
Lopevi with some ground to make
up, trying to close the gap.
Yasur very close.
Lopevi very close.
It's gonna be a race to the
finish.
Leann and Julie neck and neck.
>> Nice job.
>> Way to go, you little
snake.
It's looking good.
>> PROBST: Leann figuring this
course out.
Julie limboing through.
Leann being very careful not to
spill what could be the last bit
of juice Yasur needs.
Leann making quick work of the
course.
>> Cut through there,
that a girl.
>> PROBST: Julie on the seesaw.
>> It's all you, Julie.
It's all you.
>> You got it, Jules.
>> PROBST: But Leann is leaving
Julie behind.
>> You got it.
There you go.
>> PROBST: Coffee, croissants,
juice, love from home.
A lot at stake.
>> Good job, good job.
>> Way to go.
Drop 'em in there, Leann.
>> PROBST: That's enough.
Got to get it back to the start.
>> Get the jar!
>> Go, go, go...
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Got to get your juice
back to start.
>> Don't-don't drop.
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Got to be full when
you get back there.
Cover it.
( shouting )
>> Cover it.
>> Come on, Leann.
Hustle.
Hustle, hustle, hustle.
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Here she comes.
Go, go, go...
>> Oh!
>> Run, Jules, run.
>> Cover it with your hand.
>> PROBST: Let's see it.
>> You got it.
You got it.
You didn't spill it.
>> Let him see it, let him see
it.
>> PROBST: Let's see that black
line.
You're there.
>> Oh, that does it.
It's way above the black line.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Yasur wins Home Café
reward.
>> Good job, Jules, good
job.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Well, Lopevi, good
effort, but not enough.
No reward.
You guys can head back to camp.
Yasur, you guys needed a win.
>> Yeah, we did.
>> PROBST: You will not be
heading back to camp.
You will be heading straight up
the beach.
>> Whoa!
( cheering )
>> Home Café.
>> PROBST: Going to the Home
Café.
You'll have coffee, croissants,
juices, a little taste from
home.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
Head on up.
It's waiting for you.
>> Thanks.
( cheering, indistinct chatter )
>> Whoo!
>> Oh, my God.
( indistinct chatter )
>> Oh.
>> I'm at home!
( indistinct chatter )
>> We won the reward
challenge, and we got the
opportunity to go to the Home
Café.
We're walking up, and I see a
big bulletin board with a lot of
pictures.
>> Whoa!
( cheering )
>> Oh, my God.
>> This is me.
>> That's me on my birthday.
>> I was like, "Oh, my
God, guys, look-- pictures.
It's-it's our family, it's
everything."
>> Oh!
>> This is our first
Halloween together.
>> Oh.
>> Me and my sisters.
>> Oh, how cute.
>> That's me.
>> Is that you?
>> Oh, how cute.
>> Oh, here I am at a
family reunion.
>> Oh, my God.
>> What a little ragamuffin.
>> This is Zion.
This was three weeks ago and his
first fish.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh.
>> No.
Casey.
That's my dog.
We were pointing out family
members and dogs.
It was a really nice moment for
all of us, because getting to
share everyone's family members
with them and getting to see all
their pictures-- it just...
Oh, it just...
It touched my heart.
>> That's you with your
little brother.
>> The Kyle, yeah.
>> You are so precious.
>> Oh, I beg you, please
look at Leann.
>> Come on, now.
>> How beautiful.
>> Yay!
Coffee!
>> Huge cup of coffee.
>> Oh.
>> This is the best
moment of my life.
>> I know.
>> I'm gonna have a
croissant right now.
>> How cool is this.
>> ELIZA ( gasps ): You guys,
oh, my God, look-- letters.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God.
I got three newer letters.
>> Me, too...
>> Four.
( Eliza laughs )
>> We really needed to
win this.
There's coffee and croissants,
and we got letters from home.
( Ami laughs )
>> I'm really happy right now.
>> So am I.
>> To teamwork, to love and
to family.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Yes.
>> To Yasur,
congratulations.
>> Yeah.
( indistinct chatter )
>> Who wants coffee next?
>> French vanilla.
>> I'm really excited for this.
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
That's me.
>> My letter is from
Annie, my-my partner.
It's just full of Annie.
She's such an amazingly
beautiful human being.
>> Is that a young Scout?
( Scout sniffles )
>> It's Annie.
>> Just a beautiful picture.
( sniffling )
( crying )
>> God.
Whoa.
Both my mom and dad sent me a
letter from home, and what
really got me was, my dad said,
"Your little buddy is watching
you from above."
And that's my little brother.
>> How are you doing, Am?
( crying )
>> I'm having a rough one,
too.
( sighs )
( Ami sighs )
>> My little brother was
killed in a car accident, um,
seven, almost seven years ago.
My little brother.
That's, like, one of like my
favorite pictures in all the
world.
( sighs )
>> What's in here?
>> "Keep in mind that
though you may not be able to
change the situation, you still
have control over how you will
respond."
( sniffles )
It's funny, because just this
morning, I said, "If my temper
gets turned on, I'll burn this
whole camp down."
My wife has impeccable timing,
because all of a sudden, that's
the one thing that she mentions
on the day that I say that is,
"Rory, you got to watch your
temper and think about things."
>> I feel a very strong
bond with you.
>> I, uh...
We really need this vote
tomorrow, and I think this is
going to be...
>> Today.
>> Uh, a bunch of coffee
first thing in the morning, will
have us just running around like
squirrels anyway.
( laughter )
We're going to be wired on
coffee tomorrow morning before
we go to immunity.
Even though, uh, the pictures
and the letters really put a
human face on everybody and
their families for me, uh, it
still is about playing a game.
Anybody that knows me knows that
I always, always carry an extra
ace up my sleeve, and believe
me, even though this is a loving
moment, and we're bonding and
everything else, I ain't forgot
where they put me.
( laughter )
>> Here we go.
>> But it's a beautiful
day in Vanuatu.
( explosive rumbling )
( birds singing )
( water gently lapping )
>> Let's walk down here a
little bit further.
Well, Julie and I both knew we
needed to talk, because we're
the two females.
We will definitely be odd ones
out, because they'll want to get
rid of the two females so they
can get down to four-four-- four
women, four guys.
>> So, what are you
thinking about final four?
Have they been promising you
that?
>> They have approached
you to be one of the final four?
>> Have they done it to
you?
( laughter )
Yeah, so...
I knew they were.
>> They're playing it, ain't
they?
>> Yeah.
>> Sarge told me that
Chris and I and Sarge and Chad
would be the final four.
They turned around and they told
Julie the same exact thing.
>> I just think the guys
are going to shaft us whenever
they get a chance, no matter
what they sit there and say to
us.
>> I figured they was
playing us.
>> Yeah, of course they] are.
I approached Twila and I kind of
threw out a little reverse
psychology, and she indeed said
they had, you know, promised her
final four,
and so I said they did me also,
but they hadn't, so it
completely turned her off to
them, and now I have her on my
side currently.
I mean, I don't have any
loyalties to the women.
>> I don't either.
Between the two of us, we've got
to stay on the guys' side, but
they're worried now because the
number of the women are up.
>> Oh, of course.
All right, so, we are pretty
much pretending we're their
pawns.
>> Yes.
>> But little do they
know.
Me and Twila have a rocky
relationship, but now, I guess,
she's the only one that I'm
definitely concrete with that
I have a plan.
And I weaseled my way back in
because I knew that she was
getting sucked in with the guys,
so my plan worked, for right
now.
I guess this is our pact then to
each other.
>> You're gonna have to
have somebody to depend on.
>> Right.
>> That you can honestly depend
on.
>> And it's so unlikely to be
us.
>> Tree mail.
>> We got mail.
We've got mail.
>> Toys to play with.
"Practice, practice, practice.
Each of you has to shoot, for
one who performs poorly tonight
will get the boot."
Look.
We just got some tree mail, and
it's a sack of marbles and a
slingshot.
We're a little scared.
If we lose, there's always a
possibility to go home.
That's the downfall, and it's
definitely an option I could be
going home tonight.
>> Whatever way you hold
it, that's the way we held it
as kids.
>> I never had one.
>> Oh.
If you're right-handed, you want
to pull with the hand that you
normally are, 'cause you're
aiming like this.
Looks like we're going back to
the boys' town, back to the days
of knocking out windows and
stuff.
I mean, there's no question who
is going to win the challenge
today, I mean, Lopevi.
Yasur is like a high school team
against, you know, an SEC team.
Uh, there's no comparison.
They're gonna give us a run for
our money, but they won't win.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Not too shabby.
>> I've been a threat
since day one.
Everyone's already told me that,
so right now it's strictly a
game-based game for me.
The strategy can wait until
later.
Right now it's strictly I need
to win the immunities, because I
do not want to go to Tribal
Council.
>> Let's get ready to
rumble!
Introducing, the ladies of
Yasur, plus one.
I feel so fabulous today, I can
only speak for myself, but I am
at high rev already this
morning.
Perhaps it's the three cups of
coffee that I've had this
morning already.
( laughs )
I'm ready to run over there,
quite frankly.
This is just for direction and
aim.
>> Hey.
>> That was a good shot.
This challenge is of the utmost
importance for me because if we
lose immunity challenge today,
then I will be going home
tonight.
>> PROBST: Come on in.
All right.
Shall we get to today's
challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Give it up, Chris.
Immunity back up for grabs.
This morning in tree mail, you
received a slingshot.
I hope you practiced with it.
Here's how the challenge is
gonna work.
One tribe member at a time,
you're going to attempt to break
your tribe-colored ceramic tiles
hanging on the grid.
A tile's considered broken when
no piece is connected to more
than two wires.
Each of you will randomly be
assigned a lane on the matching
game board.
Each time you break a tile,
you'll flip over the
corresponding wooden tile on the
game board, so once you've
knocked out any given column of
ceramic tiles you will have
flipped over the corresponding
wooden tiles on the game board,
and the tribe member in that
column will move off the board
to the finish mat.
Once you're on the mat, you're
no longer a shooter.
Your goal: knock out all 20
tiles.
Lopevi, one extra member;
sitting somebody out.
Sarge sat out yesterday.
Who's it gonna be today?
>> I'm sitting out.
>> PROBST: Chris will sit out.
Chris, take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else take a spot
behind the game board, wait for
my go.
All right, first shooters up.
Rory and Chad.
Lopevi will start things.
Chad connects.
Twila.
Lopevi on the board.
Rory delivers.
>> Nice.
Way to go, Rory.
>> PROBST: that's in Leann's
column.
Leann, move forward and flip
over the corresponding tile.
Back.
>> PROBST: Next two shooters:
Ami and Julie.
>> Ooh!
Nice try.
>> This is yours, Jules.
>> PROBST: That's a miss.
Next two shooters.
No damage in that round.
Scout and Sarge.
>> Come on, Scout.
>> PROBST: Two original chiefs,
squaring off with slingshots.
There he goes.
He obliterates it.
Sarge goes back and moves his
own tile.
Lopevi takes the lead.
Scout connects.
Leann flips over another tile.
Next two shooters:
Leann and Twila.
Leann takes aim...
and connects.
Leann knocks out her own tile;
it's her third.
Yasur up 3-2.
Eliza and John.
>> Nice try, girl.
>> Come on, John.
>> PROBST: There it is.
That's Sarge.
We're tied up.
There it is.
>> There you go, baby.
She knocks her own tile.
Yasur takes the lead.
Ooh, Julie tries to bend low.
Scout's up.
Yasur leads 7-5.
( yelling )
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Another connection
from Scout.
Leann flips over her last tile.
>> Leann moves off the board and
on to the finish mat.
Yasur has their first member out
of the game.
Yasur leads 8-5.
Rory splits one.
And John connects.
Obliterates it.
Not quite enough.
Twila, like a sharp shooter.
>> Good job, good job, Twila.
>> PROBST: That's a good hit.
>> Way to go, Rory.
>> PROBST: Rory on fire.
Chad takes John's tile off.
Julie takes aim, just misses.
Rory connects with another one.
Ami flips her tile over, and
Yasur is up 17-15.
( cheering )
>> Come on, Scout.
Yes!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Scout connects with
Rory's second tile.
>> Nice.
>> Come on, Jules.
>> PROBST: Julie flips.
>> Good job, Sarge.
>> PROBST: Julie's off the
course.
>> Good job, Scout.
Come on, Rory, you're the man.
>> PROBST: Lopevi still needs
three tiles.
Yasur only needs two.
Immunity on the line.
Rory has had great success in
this challenge.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: And he continues.
>> Look at him go.
>> PROBST: Scout flips over the
next to last tile.
She is out of the game.
Rory, the only tribe member left
for Yasur.
He will shoot from here on out.
>> Take me home, Daddy,
take me home.
>> PROBST: Tribal Council
tonight; somebody going home.
John doing his best to make sure
it's not him.
>> Oh...
oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I'm out.
>> PROBST: Not enough.
>> Oh, no, I ain't.
This could be it for Yasur.
One tile left.
Rory hits it.
>> Still connected.
>> PROBST: But it's not enough.
You're still connected to three
wires.
>> Three is no problem, Rory.
>> PROBST: Chad could close the
gap for Lopevi.
And a miss.
Rory has dominated in this
challenge.
Can he win it for Yasur right
here?
>> This one's for my baby
boy.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: And he does.
Yasur wins immunity.
( all cheering )
>> Nice job.
>> Boy, the game has turned.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Give it to Rory, you
dominated.
Immunity for Yasur.
>> Whoo!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: For once, I won't be
seeing you guys at Tribal
Council.
Lopevi, I haven't seen you guys
in a while at Tribal.
I will tonight.
Sadly, Day 18 will be it for one
of you.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who's going home.
Head on back to camp.
( cheering )
( bat squeaking )
>> Awesome.
>> Rory, you're a rock star.
>> We smoked those girls.
Two in a row.
>> Let's celebrate with coffee,
shall we?
>> Yeah, how about a cup of
coffee?
>> That's what I say.
>> Whoo!
Whoo!
I know one thing for sure.
Today I rocked Ami.
I rocked the hell out of her
world today.
She could have had me as a
tight-tight friend, and she
could have eliminated me and
knocked me out the game, and
she failed to take advantage of
both those opportunities.
Now she's number one on my hit
list.
>> Rory was a rock star.
>> Rory, you were unbelievable.
>> I told you this morning
when I was shooting that thing,
I was, like, damn!
I hit the tiki three times out
of four.
>> Rory got a little cocky
with his winnings, as he well
should.
Otherwise he'd be going home,
you know?
He's earned that right.
So I'm really glad that we won,
but at the same time I looked
over at Lopevi, right, as soon
as we won, and I looked at
Julie, and it hurt.
It hurt to know that either
Julie or Twila are going home
tonight.
>> We lost the challenge
today, and we're going to Tribal
Council.
Today was the foundation, the
basis of the rest of the game
for us, but losing today meant
it's equal to them, 5-5.
The strategy of the game has
changed now.
It could go anywhere.
>> I'm not confident
Julie's staying with us, dude.
If we merge, she's going right
with the women.
>> Julie said to me
earlier this afternoon, she'd
like to get rid of John.
>> Well, yeah, there you go.
See, she's thinking it's her
turn, man.
If we merge, John's gone, she's
with the women, we're gone.
Trust in this game is huge, and
at this stage, it's even bigger,
because there's more at stake.
John, I don't trust, and Julie--
I don't believe that she would
definitely stay with Lopevi if
we merge.
As much as I don't want to keep
John around, if we keep John and
Julie goes next, we've got the
guys.
>> John has been a target
to send home ever since the game
started.
I mean, he was on the other side
with the guys, but Chad's
concerned that maybe keeping
John around a little bit longer
might be the best thing.
He doesn't have a whole lot of
trust in Julie.
>> It's up in the air,
man, with John.
I don't know.
If-if I'm convinced that Julie's
with us, then we can get rid of
John, but, I mean, otherwise,
it's a male-female thing.
The women's going to be a huge
enticement for her to go over.
Man, she's...
I can tell she's...
>> I don't think they're
so much women, or they wouldn't
have voted off Lisa.
I don't think they're hung up on
just the women.
>> ( sighs )
It's going to be tough.
It's not solid anymore right
now.
>> What does Chad say,
anything?
>> Sometimes I don't know
where Chad's coming from.
Every time, it doesn't matter
how much you talk to him, you
still go to Tribal Council with
doubt.
>> In my tribe, I don't
trust anyone.
I can't trust anyone, but I have
to at least put my faith in one
person, and I do with Chris,
because I think me and Chris can
really do some damage when it
comes down to the...
to the
dwindling of-of both tribes.
>> Just off the top of
your head, if we was leaving
right now, who would you want to
vote for?
>> See, the thing is,
I'd say Julie, but I really
don't think she'd vote on the
girls' side, so I think she's an
asset to have later on.
And I think with-with Chad, he
gets the sympathy vote.
Sounds bad, but it's true, you
know?
>> I'm coming to grips with...
You know, I understand what
you're saying.
>> If it ever came down
to him and one of us in the
finals, final two, he'd get it
in a...
in a heartbeat, because,
you know...
I thought of Chad since day one,
because he's type of guy that
just gets by every time; not
just gets by on the vote, but
just gets by without anyone
noticing him.
And Chad can seriously get some
sympathy points, which he's
great at, because he does have
one leg, and he's doing amazing,
but we can't handle any sympathy
points against us, so he's got
to go now.
What's up with you guys?
>> Stacking some wood, boy.
>> Oh, yeah?
>> What are you doing?
>> Wondering which one of
us is going home tonight.
>> That's what I came
to tell you.
Chad.
>> So, you want Chad tonight?
>> Yeah, Chad tonight.
>> It's not going to be
me or her?
>> It's not going...
I swear on my life that it's not
you two.
>> Go ahead, hon.
I'll be there later.
>> But me-me and Chris
are being seriously true on
this, and we just think we-we
could all be tighter with this
group.
>> Julie, are you comfortable
with that-- voting off Chad?
>> Depends on, uh, Sarge,
right, if he's down?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, even if Sarge
isn't, that means it's
everyone against...
>> Oh, three against...
>> It would be...
it'd be
us four against Chad.
>> Yeah, us four.
I take Twila's word, 'cause she
is a rough redneck, and to me,
all rough rednecks that I have
met are pretty loyal.
At this point, everyone could be
completely playing everyone, so
people are either going with
what I said, or people are going
to vote me off, so I-I can't
stress enough that tonight is
the night-- for me, anyways-- to
figure out where I stand in this
game.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Tribal
Council.
Haven't seen you guys in a
while.
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: So, Chris, everything
seemed to be going so well for
Lopevi, and then out of nowhere,
back-to-back losses.
What happened?
>> I don't know.
You know, it seemed like when,
you know, we-we-we-we went on
four wins in a row.
It seemed like we were
dominating.
It didn't even seem like it was
close, but today, it was close.
I mean, you know, they-they beat
us by a couple, uh, but that's
all it takes, and that's why
we're here and they're not.
>> PROBST: So, Chad, what was
the reaction when you got back
to camp?
You guys haven't had to
contemplate voting somebody out
in a long time.
>> Right.
When we are
going off to do our little wood
gathering and pot scrubbing,
you're aware of who's going with
who, and if you're alone, or
maybe you shouldn't be alone,
and, you know, so there's a lot
of posturing going on, you know.
We're scrambling here before,
uh, Tribal Council.
>> PROBST: Chris, does everybody
have a role in this tribe?
>> I think to a certain
degree, yeah, everybody's got a
role.
Um, everybody does something
that benefits the tribe during
the day.
There's always a time when we're
going to need to eat, and, uh,
we're going to need firewood,
and there's always someone
willing to step up and do that.
I think it's a team effort.
>> PROBST: Sarge, what does
Twila do well?
>> Um, Twila is the, uh,
wonder for, um, exotic foods.
She is the preparer of meals,
and she's constantly going to
get firewood.
She-she just...
she does
everything.
>> PROBST: John, what could
Twila do better?
>> Um, the thing with Twila is,
she really is the workhorse.
Her and Sarge are the two
workhorses.
Um, as far as do better, I would
love to see her take naps.
I would...
I would love it.
I would not feel distressed
around camp if I saw Twila say,
"Hey, let's kick back and take a
nap," 'cause I'm the number one
napper go-going.
I mean, I like taking naps, and-
and I never see her take little
catnaps ever.
>> PROBST: So, if you look over,
and you see the workhorse never
taking a nap, how do you ever
justify taking a nap?
>> I thank you very much.
>> Because... because
whenever-whenever something...
I'm asked to do anything, I-I
will do it.
We all do our roles.
I mean, I-I might take more
naps, but she could take naps,
too.
It's-it's okay to take a nap.
That's the thing.
We don't always need to be
working.
>> PROBST: So, Chad, tell me
about life at camp, because
you're living with these people,
but you are competing against
them.
How do you know if you're
getting to know somebody well or
being played?
>> I think that there's a...
there's a very good general
first impression and a good way
of someone perceiving someone
else that gets down to the core
level who that person is, and if
you feel like you're perceptive
enough that you can get to that
core level quickly, then I think
can you trust them, unless
they're of someone who's
completely manipulative and
someone that can...
>> PROBST: Imagine that in this
game.
>> ...that can lie and
cheat very well, but I feel like
I can pick up on that.
I really do.
>> PROBST: Julie, think this
tribe trusts you?
>> Well, the time spent
together has been very telling,
and, um, I think we've gelled
really well, especially with
winning, and it is just a matter
of meshing well and the energies
put together.
And, um, there has been doubt
and there probably still is, but
hopefully, you know, even with
this vote, um, the proof will be
there.
>> PROBST: Chris, what are you
basing your vote on?
>> Um, I'm basing...
I'm basing
my vote on a couple things.
First of all, I'm basing my-my
vote on trust.
Trust is hard to come by in this
game, and sometimes, you think
you have it, and-and you turn
around, and that wink or that
nod kind of puts that trust in
doubt.
Um, I'm also basing my-my vote
on my future in the game, who's
going to benefit me or benefit
the people that, you know, I'm
playing the game with or aligned
with.
>> PROBST: With that, it is time
to vote.
Sarge, you're up.
>> I'm afraid you might
sneak by some more, and I need
you to go.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: John.
Chad.
One vote John, one vote Chad.
John.
Two votes John, one vote Chad.
That's three votes John, one
vote Chad.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu: John.
That's four, and that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
John, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Take it easy.
>> PROBST: Well, John said it
himself.
Tonight is one of those nights
when you find out who you can
trust and who you can't.
He just found out the hard way.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time
on Survivor...
>> Uno, dos, tres.
>> PROBST: The girls corrupt
Sarge.
>> Tan that ass.
>> Sarge, what are you doing?!
>> Is the coffee ready to go?
>> What a worthless crew.
>> PROBST: Rory reaches his
breaking point.
>> What a completely
worthless crew.
I'm ready to get the hell out of
Yasur.
>> PROBST: And everything is
turned on its head.
>> Uh-oh.
>> Well, I came, I played,
I lost, and I'm a little bitter.
I'd love to say I walk out of
here with no regrets, but I'd
have to say I'm shocked, 'cause
I really wouldn't have turned on
any of you guys, but you guys
turned on me.
Um, Chris, best of luck.
I hope you win.
Sarge, hope you come in second.
Everybody else, hope you lose.
( chuckles )