>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
the tribes received a visit from
Vanuatu locals.
(speaking native language)
>> JOHN K.: One chief?
>> TRAVIS: One chief.
>> JEFF: Lopevi chose Sarge and
Yasur chose Scout as chiefs.
And then, an earthquake rocked
the island.
>> LEANN: Holy....
>> TRAVIS: Whoa!
>> CHAD Good going, bro.
Yeah!
>> JEFF: At the reward
challenge, Sarge and Scout, the
two chiefs, divided the tribes,
mixing up the men and women.
>> SCOUT: Jules.
>> JEFF: When it shook out,
Julie and Twila had joined the
Lopevi tribe as the only two
women, and Bubba and Rory joined
Yasur as the only two men.
Go!
During the challenge, even
though Chris dropped a marker
for Lopevi, Yasur still couldn't
catch up.
Ami can't do it.
Lopevi wins reward.
>> JOHN K.: Great job today,
guys.
>> JEFF: The new Lopevi tribe
enjoyed chips and beer at the
waterfall, giving Julie and
Twila a chance to get to know
the men.
>> JULIE: Me and Twila are
trying to weasel our way in
there.
>> JEFF: At Yasur, Rory and
Bubba tried to fit in with the
women.
>> TRAVIS: But being in a tribe
with a bunch of women-- it does
make you nervous, 'cause one
wrong move, and they'll vote you
out.
>> JEFF: At the immunity
challenge...
>> TRAVIS: Think about the
merge.
>> JEFF: ...Bubba tried to
communicate with his old tribe
mates, but Ami caught the
exchange.
Go!
The challenge was close.
>> RORY: Come on, come on!
>> JEFF: But Lopevi came out on
top.
Lopevi wins immunity!
>> LEA: Whoo!
>> JEFF: At Tribal Council,
Bubba was on the hot seat, but
Rory learned he was the original
target.
>> AMI: Bubba, you weren't going
to be the first one that we had
picked if we did lose to go.
>> JEFF: When the votes came in,
Bubba paid the ultimate price
for his big mistake.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
♪ ♪
>> SCOUT: Thanks for working
this fire.
>> RORY: Yeah, well, apparently,
I got to stay warm.
>> SCOUT: Well, what does that
mean?
>> RORY: Y'all need to leave me
alone right now.
>> ELIZA: Okay.
>> RORY: 'Cause y'all have shown
me something that I'm not real
impressed with, and perhaps for
the... for the peace and
tranquility of this tribe, it
would be best for me to hold my
tongue until tomorrow morning.
Bubba and I both knew that it
was going to be one or the other
of us that was going to be
leaving tonight at Tribal
Council.
The ladies made a mistake in
telling me that I would've been
eliminated before Bubba was, and
so what I'm going to basically
do is I'm going to play it up.
I came to y'all straight up.
I don't know if you guys are so
smoked in that you don't even
see honesty when it comes right
at y'all.
You got me up on the auction
block.
>> SCOUT: No, don't say I got
you up on the auction block.
>> RORY: Well, you certainly
judged me quick enough.
>> SCOUT: The judgment is that
you're sitting right here in
camp.
>> RORY: The thing I need to
watch is I can't push these
ladies too far.
I just kind of got to balance it
and push 'em just far enough to
give myself a little bit of an
opening.
My thing is to come off as the
upset, angry brother who is
welcomed back into the fold.
Your little crew just made a
decision about whether or not
y'all want a teammate or not,
and if you don't want a
teammate, then-then be woman
enough to let me know.
>> SCOUT: All right.
That's a deal.
Rory would like to tell
everybody off right now, but
that would just seal his fate.
He's had a fit and fell in it
and sitting over there on his
pity pot, so hopefully, he'll
wipe his ass and get off and get
over it and, you know, start a
new day, and let's see what we
can make of it.
(bird cawing)
(man grunting)
>> TWILA: I can't get it up on
my shoulder.
You guys are taller than I am.
I'll help as much as I can.
>> LEA: My new tribe is awesome.
It's a blessing to have women
around, not that we need 'em.
I'm not saying that we... it'd-
it'd be any different, um, one
way or another, but, I mean,
it's good to have 'em.
>> JULIE: Do tell.
>> LEA: No, no, not this one.
Not to you, especially.
>> CHRIS: It's interesting
having a pretty girl playing the
game, 'cause somebody like that
can fly underneath the radar and
sweet talk their way into the
final five, and then, you know,
boom, next thing you know,
they're sitting there waiting to
win the money.
>> JULIE: You need to put lotion
on your damn shoulders.
Today is my second morning with
the new tribe.
Now it's more relaxed but
definitely uncertain.
Women are more passive-
aggressive than men are.
I don't know.
And, you know, that's all you
would get over at Yasur.
>> TWILA: I can't wait to see
who is gone and what the reward
is.
>> JULIE: I'll just laugh if one
of the guys is gone.
>> TWILA: I'll laugh if Eliza's
gone.
>> CHAD: Who thinks what?
All right, who do you think is
going to be gone, Sarge?
>> LEA: Uh, Bubba's safe.
Everybody loves Bubba.
>> TWILA: I think everybody kind
of loves Scout.
There ain't no doubt about it.
She's the older, wiser one.
>> JULIE: You can't... Yeah.
You can't not appreciate her.
>> LEA: So we're supposed to
love the older person, so we
love Twila.
>> TWILA: Thank you.
Oh, God, thank you.
You had to point that out,
didn't you?
>> LEA: Yup.
>> JULIE: What are you thinking?
>> TWILA: Oh, I don't know what
to think.
They're being real nice, but
we're still the outsiders.
>> JULIE: Completely.
>> TWILA: Julie and I actually
talk now.
That's more than what I can say
we ever did over the other
tribe, 'cause I never actually
talked to her over there.
We got to keep winning
challenges.
The best bet for us is to keep
winning the challenges.
That's it.
>> JULIE: I know.
>> TWILA: Being the only two
women over here and four men,
we're odd out.
We're both vulnerable.
We know it.
You know, they could be blowing
smoke up her ass just like
they're blowing smoke up my ass.
You know, I don't know.
>> SCOUT: Tree mail, Yasur.
>> LISA: It's a pig.
>> AMI: Is that a pig?
>> Oh, my God.
>> LISA: "You are likely to
become exhausted, so here's to
mud in your eye."
Oh, God.
"It's all for creature comforts
to help improve your sty."
>> ELIZA: Reward. Yeah.
>> It's reward.
>> LISA: Maybe with pigs.
>> LEANN: Oh, let's wrestle one
of those suckers.
>> SCOUT: Pig wrestling.
Yasur, let's get our butts out
there.
Come here, Rory.
>> AMI: Rory, come on over here.
>> SCOUT: That's a pretty
picture right there.
>> Yeah.
>> SCOUT: One, two, three.
>> ALL: Yasur!
>> LISA: Whoo-hoo-hoo!
>> RORY: I think we should, uh,
have a conversation then.
>> SCOUT: Okay.
>> RORY: First off, my apologies
to all of you for the horrible,
horrible things that I said to
you in my mind last night.
When I get angry, I tend to
become extraordinarily hurtful.
I have come to you all with the
expectation that you all would
give me a fair shot, and I have
done my damnedest to prove to
you all where my loyalties lie.
At this point, I can't go back
to Lopevi.
I can't, because Bubba's gone,
and what's going to be their
first thought?
I sold Bubba out.
So this is where I'm at right
now.
Your sty is my sty, but I will
not continue to slave around
camp if I do not have a shot at
making it through Tribal
Council.
My speech was so cheesy that I
couldn't even believe I was
saying it myself, you know?
I mean, afterwards, I was
sitting there thinking, "Man,
there's no way in hell these
ladies bought any of that," but
maybe they did, and if I could
sway 'em just a little bit
toward favor for me, you got to
do what you got to do.
>> JEFF: Yasur, come on in.
Lopevi, get your first look at
the new Yasur tribe.
>> CHAD: Whoa...
>> JEFF: Bubba voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
>> CHRIS: Whoa.
>> JEFF: Okay.
Shall we get to the challenge?
>> LEA: Yeah-ha.
>> JEFF: On the islands of
Vanuatu, pigs are highly valued.
They're currency and they're a
status symbol, and right now,
they have a value to you.
>> CHAD: Yeah.
>> JEFF: Today's challenge is
for reward, and you're going to
get good and muddy as a result.
>> JULIE: Yeah.
>> JEFF: We have assembled a
pen, filled it with pigs.
Your goal: catch the pigs.
Five tribe members will be pig
catchers.
They're responsible for catching
two pigs each.
You can grab two at once or one
at a time.
One person will be a gatekeeper.
Their job is to make sure the
pigs you catch remain caught.
First tribe to collect ten of
their tribe-colored pigs wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> JEFF: Steak and eggs.
>> LEA: Oh, yeah! Yeah!
Good God!
>> ELIZA: Oh, my gosh.
>> JEFF: Six big steaks, six
eggs, skillet to fry 'em in,
lots of ingredients to make 'em
taste nice and good.
>> Whoo!
>> LEA: That's too good, buddy.
>> TWILA: Oh, man, that's
awesome.
>> JEFF: Lopevi, who's your
gatekeeper?
>> JULIE: Okay.
>> JEFF: Julie's going to be the
gatekeeper.
Yasur, it's Scout. All right.
Take your spots. Wait for my go.
(squealing)
(snorting)
>> JEFF: Here we go for reward.
It's time to get dirty.
Survivors ready.
Go.
>> Oh!
>> JEFF: Rory and John first
out.
There go the pigs.
(all shouting)
Rory's got one.
John has got one.
>> RORY: Through the gate,
through the gate.
(shouting)
>> JEFF: One for Yasur, one for
Lopevi.
John back out.
>> JULIE: Nice, nice.
>> JEFF: John, back with two.
(squealing)
(pig snorting and squealing)
>> AMI: It's okay.
Mama take good care of you.
>> JEFF: Ami with her first pig.
Lisa out on the course.
>> TWILA: Dive at him.
>> JULIE: Come on, Chris, come
on, Chris!
>> JEFF: Chris has one for
Lopevi.
>> There you go, baby.
(squealing)
>> JEFF: Lopevi with a three-two
lead.
Chris going again.
(pig squealing)
Lisa's got to get back here.
>> Come on...
Come on, come on...
>> JEFF: Chris has got his
second.
Lisa's got a big pig, as big as
she is.
Yasur ties it, three-three.
Lopevi now up, four-three.
Chris has both his pigs.
(squealing)
Eliza and Chad out on the
course.
Lopevi leads four-three.
>> LEA: Go, go, go.
>> JEFF: Eliza having trouble.
>> RORY: Go, go get him.
>> Let's go, hustle.
(all shouting)
(pig squealing)
>> RORY: Come here.
Come on back over here.
>> JEFF: Chad has a pig for
Lopevi.
Going back out for his second.
>> Get him!
>> AMI: Come on, Eliza.
Come on, come on.
>> JEFF: Still no pig for Eliza.
>> ELIZA: Does somebody else
want to go?
>> RORY: Get him, get him.
>> JEFF: Lopevi leads,
five-three.
>> RORY: Go, go, get him.
>> Come on, Eliza.
>> JEFF: Chad has his second pig
and a lot of mud.
Eliza trying.
She can't do it.
(all shouting)
Leann on the course.
Lopevi leads Yasur, six-three.
>> Come on, pig.
>> TWILA: Come on, pig.
>> JEFF: Twila on the course.
Leann not messing around.
She's got a pig.
(all shouting)
Leann has her first pig.
Going for another one.
Twila's got one cornered.
She's got him.
>> Good job.
>> Yeah, good job.
>> Good job, Twila.
>> JEFF: Lopevi leads,
seven-four.
Twila going back out.
Leann coming out, Rory back in.
Lopevi leads, seven, four.
Rory wasting no time.
(pig squealing)
He's got his second pig.
But can he hold on?
(Rory shouting)
>> JEFF: Rory lost his pig.
>> Yeah!
>> TWILA: Yeah.
Yeah!
>> JEFF: Twila's got her pig.
>> JULIE: Steak tonight, baby.
Steak tonight!
>> JEFF: Eight-four.
Lopevi leads.
It's down to Sarge.
Lopevi with an eight-four lead.
Sarge needs to get two pigs.
>> LEA: Yeah, pig, pig, pig.
Here, pig. Here, pig.
Here, here.
(pig squealing)
(people shouting)
>> JEFF: Rory has one for Yasur.
We're at nine-five.
Lopevi needs one more pig.
It's up to Sarge.
Sarge going for the last pig for
Lopevi.
(shouting)
(squealing)
Can he keep him?
Ami has one for Yasur.
This is it.
If Sarge crosses, Lopevi wins.
>> JULIE: Yeah, come on!
>> JEFF: Lopevi wins reward!
>> LEA: Whoo-hoo!
(indistinct chatter)
>> JEFF: Yasur, good effort, not
enough.
Head on out, get your stuff,
head back to camp.
Lopevi, nice work.
Steak and eggs waiting for you.
Come get it.
>> Yeah!
(birds singing)
>> TWILA: Eggs.
>> LEA: Meat.
>> TWILA: We slaughtered 'em.
>> CHRIS: We continue to win.
We continue to stay.
>> JOHN K.: No, Sarge.
I hear you.
>> TWILA: We kicked their ass.
We-We kicked their ass, and we
done good.
Whoo-ee!
(laughs)
We kissed some ass.
I just loved it.
>> LEA: Man.
>> TWILA: Them prissy ass girls
didn't want to get their
fingernails dirty.
>> JOHN K.: They'll say, "I
can't do it, I can't do it."
>> TWILA: I loved it.
>> LEA: Beef-- it's what's for
dinner.
>> CHAD: Yeah.
>> LEA: You ready?
>> TWILA: Yup.
I like mine pink in the middle.
I don't like it bloody runny,
but I want it pink in the
middle.
>> LEA: Okay, medium well.
Does anybody want Cajun spice on
their steak?
>> JOHN K.: I do.
>> LEA (laughs): All right.
Now I'm on cloud nine.
I'm, like, it's party time.
Steaks that thick.
>> TWILA: Yup.
Let mine up there.
This is going to be freaking
great.
>> LEA: Couldn't get no better
than this.
Two weeks without meat, and I'm
just, like... I'm pumped.
I'm really pumped right now.
Raise the doggone roof.
>> LEA: Definitely feels like
home right now.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> TWILA: Oh, man. Hmm.
>> LEA: Damn.
>> CHRIS: This is great.
>> LEA: This is better than sex
right now.
>> LEA: Oh, dude.
>> JULIE: Man's delirious.
>> LEA: Dude, man.
>> TWILA: So you think the
ladies are disappointed?
>> JULIE: Um...
>> CHRIS: Oh, my gosh.
If I was them, I'd be crying.
>> TWILA: Do you think they was
wishing they was...
>> LEA: Bubba, man-- he was a
cool dude.
>> JULIE: Either way, even if
they had Bubba, I mean, Eliza
says she couldn't do it.
>> Yeah, I don't how to stay in
the lead, but...
>> LEA: I know, but how do you
say I can't do it?
>> CHRIS: I can't...
I-I didn't hear her say that,
but I would be absolutely pissed
if someone said...
...and they didn't try,
continue to try.
>> JULIE: I didn't see her...
I didn't see her try.
Maybe she did.
>> TWILA: She didn't.
Well, not that I seen.
>> They'll can her next.
>> CHRIS: I couldn't walk the
balance beam, but at least I
tried.
>> JULIE: She wasn't out there
long...
>> TWILA: All right.
>> CHRIS: I looked like an
idiot, but at least I tried.
>> TWILA: I don't understand the
way of thinking.
If I was over there, I thought
they screwed up.
Why would you keep somebody like
Eliza and not keep your muscle?
I don't understand that.
(explosive rumbling)
>> LEANN: It was really, really,
really a hard challenge to lose.
I felt like just going home,
washing off and going to bed.
It would have been nice to
win...
the pig challenge.
>> ELIZA: Sweetie, is my back
good, by the way?
>> LEANN: I was a little
bothered that Eliza didn't want
to... it seemed like she didn't
want to get dirty or something.
I don't know.
She was the only one to not get
a pig at all.
Um... did she even get dirty?
>> RORY: I hate losing.
>> LISA: I do, too.
I hate losing bad.
>> RORY: Damn, I just wanted a
steak.
>> LISA: Okay, and that's the
third loss.
We've lost the Pringles, we lost
immunity, and we lost this.
>> RORY: And if we lose
tomorrow, the next immunity
challenge, I'm going home, and
you guys are sunk.
>> LISA: Yup.
>> RORY: You know, I'm-I'm the
one that's next on the auction
block, uh, to leave the island,
but the fact of the matter is,
Eliza's... she's killing this
team, she's killing our tribe.
>> LISA: Anybody want some?
>> ELIZA: You guys, I'm sorry
again.
>> LISA: Don't worry about it.
We have good cabbage soup
tonight.
Really, don't worry about it.
Do not worry about it.
>> ELIZA: I know, but I was
awful. Like, I was...
>> RORY: You tried.
>> LISA: Do not worry about it.
>> RORY: Twila certainly
looks...
>> LISA: Don't worry about it.
>> LEANN: I didn't see her.
>> LISA: Okay?
>> RORY: That girl will stand...
>> LISA: Oh, do not...
Don't worry about it.
You know what?
It's just a steak.
I'm aggravated, 'cause I think
she's the reason we lost.
In fact, I know she is.
She's the reason we lost.
>> AMI: You can cry.
It's okay, 'cause I'm sure
there'll be times when I cry.
(Eliza sniffles)
I'm, like...
(laughs) I suck.
I'm sure there'll be those
times.
>> ELIZA: Oh!
>> AMI: We'll all have those
times.
>> ELIZA: I'm just...
not used to...
...being bad at things, you
know?
Like I... I know it sounds so
stupid.
I mean...
>> AMI: So...
Yes?
>> ELIZA: I...
I like Scout as a person.
I wish she wasn't here.
I just think that if she wasn't
here, that would have been a
challenge where I would have
been able to be gatekeeper.
Because it's, like, because we
have Scout, and she's got her
knee, and, you know, it's just
always, like...
And then, it's easy for her to
come back and be, like, "Good
job guys."
And, like, you know...
And then, I feel like, because I
know I didn't do a good job,
and...
(sniffling)
>> AMI: Like, right now, honey,
I feel like you're coming up
with a lot of excuses.
>> ELIZA: I am. I know.
>> AMI: You are totally capable.
You were so 100% capable of
doing the challenge today.
You're not giving yourself as
much credit as you deserve, and
saying, "You know what?
Screw it.
"I could have done that today,
and I just didn't so it, and
next time I'm gonna give it
everything I got."
>> ELIZA: And I-I want to
believe that we can win a
challenge against this all-male
plus Julie and Twila tribe.
(sniffles)
And yet, I don't think we can.
>> AMI: You need to get that out
of your head, 'cause I'm not
about ready to go down because
there's a bunch of muscles on
the other team.
>> SCOUT: There we go.
>> LISA: Right here inside?
>> SCOUT: No. Let me see.
Hold that a second.
>> LISA: Perfect.
>> RORY: Every woman on this
team understands how much damage
Eliza did today, and I think,
uh, Eliza's reeling right now,
and she should be, because this
tribe realizes that if they keep
her on here, they're signing
their own death warrant, and
right now they need somebody
strong, and I'm the strongest
resource available to them, and
the only thing that I've hoped
for is for there to be a little
fissure, a little tiny crack in
that union of women, and I think
I just found my little tiny
crack.
>> JULIE: I'd like to tan my
ass.
>> CHAD: You know, I think the
coed thing is working really
well for our tribe now because I
think it's just a morale thing.
It was getting a little stagnant
there for a while.
>> JULIE: I like flirting.
I could flirt all day long.
It just comes naturally.
It's just like with me,
I don't know.
It's how I connect with people,
Just a natural thing.
Just my butt though. Ah...
whatever.
>> LEA: Today Julie was
sunbathing her buttocks region.
I mean, I didn't want to look at
it too much, but, uh, it looked
pretty good.
I mean, I took a quick peek but
I wasn't going to stare at it,
but it looked real good.
I mean, if you got it, sunbathe
it.
>> JULIE: If we lose and the
guys are desperate, they're
going to need to recruit
somebody.
Twila's my ally, but I think
she's aligning with the older
guys.
You know, I don't know.
She's... she's up to something.
I can sense it.
>> LEA: You ready?
>> TWILA: Yep.
>> LEA: Here's the machete.
>> TWILA: Okay, suck in a little
bit more to the tree.
Little bit more.
>> LEA: Here you go.
Ow, ow, ow, don't grind.
I would take Twila as a best
friend for the next 20 years
over any of the women in Yasur.
>> TWILA: I still can't reach
it, baby, still not tall enough.
>> LEA: Okay, I'm going tall.
I need your heel. Okay, there.
Now, step up with that foot,
and I'm gonna get the other one.
I could pal around with Twila,
I'd drink a beer with Twila, I'd
go to the race with Twila.
>> TWILA: Coming down.
>> LEA: I also would put a dress
on Twila and go out to dinner
with her because she is a lady.
>> TWILA: Well, Julie asked me
if I'd go back, if I'd vote with
the women.
>> LEA: Uh-huh. What'd you tell
her?
>> TWILA: I told her I didn't
know, I didn't think so.
>> LEA: What did she say?
>> TWILA: She said she didn't
know either, after the way it
was done and the way she was
treated there at first.
She didn't know either.
>> LEA: Well, she'd be a fool to
go against us.
She'd be a fool, because we're
going to keep her around as long
as Lopevi's strong.
Chris, Chad and I, we're three.
Three is a real odd number.
Four is always better, and so I
went ahead and gave her my word,
and I said, "Twila you've got my
word as a man you are in the
four till the end, no matter
what."
We didn't want to take John.
We don't trust John.
>> TWILA: No, I don't trust
John.
>> LEA: So, we needed someone a
little bit more mature that
knows what it means to give your
word.
>> TWILA: I do.
I don't know.
At this point, you know, hell,
they're all lying sacks of ...
It don't make any...
You know, you can't trust
nobody, but right now, I have to
trust somebody.
>> LEA: Oh, I give you my word
that the four is strong until it
comes to four, and then it's
whatever.
>> TWILA: Every man and women
for their selves.
>> LEA: Yeah.
>> TWILA: I'm telling you, I
just have a good feeling we're
going to keep winning, guy.
I really am not worried.
Are they telling Julie the same
thing they're telling me?
I might be the next one to go,
and they're just playing me as a
fool, I don't know.
>> JEFF: First things first.
Chris, take back immunity.
Immunity back up for grabs.
Today's immunity challenge is
going to wear you out.
Four tribe members will start on
a floating platform, where you
will find eight wooden tiki
pieces.
Each tribe member must transport
two tiki pieces to the beach by
moving them along a rope through
a water obstacle course.
The first stage, you must
maneuver the pieces around an
outrigger canoe.
For the second stage, you must
get the pieces and yourself up
and over a wall.
For the third stage you'll go
underwater and maneuver the
pieces through three hitching
posts.
And for the final stage you must
maneuver the pieces through a
truss.
Once you have the pieces up on
the beach and in their trough,
the next person can go.
Once all eight pieces are in the
trough, the final two tribe
members assemble the tiki.
First tribe to assemble the
tiki correctly wins immunity,
guaranteed one more day out
here.
Losing tribe, Tribal Council
tonight.
Somebody going home.
Yasur, which two people are
going to be solving the puzzle?
Scout?
>> SCOUT: And Lisa.
>> JEFF: And Lisa.
Lopevi, which two are going to
solve the puzzle?
>> TWILA: Me and Chad.
>> JEFF: Chad and Twila.
Four swimmers head out.
For immunity.
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> ELIZA: Go Yasur!
>> JEFF: Chris and Ami the first
two in the water.
>> ELIZA: Go, Yasur, go!
>> JEFF: Chris starting toward
the wall.
>> SCOUT: Come on, Ami.
>> JEFF: Chris to the wall
first; Ami right behind.
>> RORY: Come on Ames.
>> JEFF: Got to get the pieces
up and over the wall, and you've
got to get over the wall.
Ami taking both pieces at once.
Chris going one at a time.
Chris is over the wall first.
Ami has one, two.
Chris heading down to his first
sawhorse.
Three to get through.
(participants cheering)
>> LEANN: Yeah, Ami, you're
awesome!
>> JEFF: Chris has both pieces
through.
Heading to the truss.
Neither tribe member giving up,
but both worn out.
Chris heads into the truss.
Chris is through the truss.
>> CHAD: Yeah.
>> TWILA: There you go, Chris,
there you go.
>> JEFF: Ami making her way
through the truss.
You're good, man, it's all you.
>> Get them up there, Chris.
>> JOHN K.: Go for it! Go!
Go for it! Come on! Move it!
>> JEFF: Ami's through the
truss.
>> Go, Ami!
>> JEFF: Keep fighting, Ami!
You guys are in this.
Rory in the water.
Sarge making his way up the
wall, Rory making up a lot of
time at the outrigger.
>> LEANN: Go, Rory, go!
>> JEFF: Rory heading to the
wall.
Sarge has his second piece over
the wall.
>> TWILA: Come on, Sarge!
>> JEFF: And he's up and over.
Sarge heading toward the
hitching post.
Rory at the wall, close behind.
>> JULIE: Keep going, Sarge.
>> Let's go, Sarge!
>> SCOUT: Way to go, Rory.
>> JEFF: Rory is closing the
gap.
>> CHAD: Come on, Sarge, you can
do it!
>> JEFF: Rory staying under for
a long time at the hitching
post.
Rory trying to make up some
time.
>> Rory!
>> JEFF: Sarge has both pieces
through.
He's heading to the truss.
Rory has both pieces through.
He's looking to pass Sarge at
the truss.
>> JULIE: Come on, Sarge!
(all shouting encouragement)
>> JEFF: They're neck and neck.
Rory is first through the
truss.
>> AMI: Come on, Rory.
Bring it home!
>> JEFF: He's got the lead back
for Yasur.
Sarge right behind him.
>> TWILA: Go, Sarge!
Pick it up and run with it.
Pick it up and run.
Go!
>> JEFF: Go, go!
>> Go, go!
>> JEFF: We are dead even after
two.
>> Go, Jules, go!
>> JEFF: Leann right behind
Julie.
>> CHRIS: Go, Julie! Come on!
>> JEFF: Julie has both pieces
over the wall and now she's got
to get over it.
>> AMI: Come on, Leann.
You can get ahead here.
>> JEFF: Rough water making it
difficult.
>> RORY: Leann, get your breath
and do them both at once!
>> JEFF: Leann struggling.
>> SCOUT: One more big breath,
Leann.
>> ELIZA: Go, Leann, go.
You can do it. You can do it.
You can do it. Yes, you can.
>> JEFF: Leann is exhausted.
Julie's through the three
hitching posts, heading to the
truss.
>> JOHN K.: Good job, Julie,
come on!
>> TWILA: Pick 'em up, Jules,
pick 'em up.
>> JULIE: I'm picking them up.
>> TWILA: Yeah, all right.
>> JEFF: John in the water with
the final two tiki pieces for
Lopevi.
Leann is still stuck at the
hitching post.
>> RORY: Go!
>> AMI: You can do it.
>> JEFF: Leann finally heads
back down.
John, he's over the wall with a
cannonball.
John and Leann now both at the
hitching post.
Lopevi has almost lapped Yasur.
Leann getting a second wind...
But it's not enough.
John has passed Leann.
He's through the hitching post,
heading to the truss.
It's the final leg for Lopevi.
>> Go, Leann!
>> JEFF: John is through the
truss with the last two tiki
pieces for Lopevi.
>> Bring 'em up, John.
>> JEFF: Start putting it
together.
Twila and Chad working on the
puzzle.
Leann still fighting with the
hitching post.
Eliza still waiting for her
shot.
It may never come.
>> TWILA: Go ahead, king it,
crown it.
>> JEFF: With that, Lopevi wins
immunity.
>> JOHN K.: Great job, great
job, great job.
>> LEA: High-fives. High-fives.
>> TWILA: I'm proud of you.
>> AMI: Nice job.
>> JEFF: Lopevi, immunity.
No Tribal Council tonight.
You're safe at least one more
day.
Congratulations.
>> TWILA: Thank you.
>> JEFF: Yasur, obviously a very
tough challenge.
You guys gave it a great effort,
not enough.
Tonight the seventh person will
be voted out of this game, and
they're coming from your tribe.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Head on back to camp.
>> Whoo!
>> Ow!
(bird singing)
>> LEANN: Oh, my God, I hate
more than anything letting my
team down.
And I... I really didn't want
anybody to go home.
And it was so draining.
That's why I'm an emotional
mess.
>> ELIZA: Seriously though,
seriously, how strong were you?
>> LEANN: I just feel so bad.
>> ELIZA: Trust me.
I know how you feel and
everybody has...
I mean, don't worry.
>> LEANN: No, I feel as if I
should go home because I screwed
up so bad.
But at the same time,
I so don't want to go home.
>> SCOUT: Getting to get over
it?
How long does it take you to get
over it?
>> LEANN: I just want to be here
tomorrow.
>> ELIZA: I don't think there's
any doubt in anyone's mind that
you will be.
>> LEANN: You guys make me feel
like the best loser ever.
And then I feel guilty because
if I don't go home, someone else
is going to go home because of
me.
There's nothing good about it.
>> AMI: There we go.
You want me to go get more
manioc?
>> LISA: Yeah, yeah, we're going
to...
>> AMI: Is that all right?
>> SCOUT: I'm gonna go with you.
>> AMI: I can go really quick.
Why... do we need three people
to go?
>> AMI: Oh, in case what?
(Lisa chuckles)
Lisa said she wanted to know
where the manioc was just in
case I wasn't around, and I just
found that quite interesting.
Kind of like an oops, did that
really just come out of your
mouth?
That's pretty funny, Lisa.
You want to go with me just in
case I'm not here for you...
That's funny.
That's what she just said to me.
>> LISA: That's not what I said.
I said just in case somebody
needs to go get it.
>> AMI: Right.
I think Lisa is so sneaky.
I don't trust her.
I watch.
Watching is the best way to
figure it out, and I don't
really love what I see when I
watch her.
>> LISA: What are you feeling
tonight?
>> AMI: I don't feel comfortable
voting for Rory, no matter what,
because I feel like he's really
put himself out there.
>> LISA: Yeah, I want him to be
a part.
>> SCOUT: Yeah, absolutely.
>> SCOUT: Which, you know, my
vote is going to be for Liza.
>> AMI: Hmm.
>> SCOUT: I mean, ultimately,
right?
>> AMI: I'm not voting for
Eliza.
After Lisa's comment, I'd vote
for Lisa though before I vote
for Eliza.
>> SCOUT: This Lisa?
>> AMI: Yeah, this Lisa.
Your comment was just rude.
>> LISA: About what?
>> AMI: About, "Oh, I want to go
'cause just in case you're not
around," like...
>> LISA: Oh, honey, I swear to
you...
Wait a minute, Ami.
>> SCOUT: Hey, Ami.
>> LISA: Ami...
(Scout and Lisa talking)
>> AMI: I'm being honest.
>> LISA: Ami, you're the last
one that's going to go, babe,
you know.
>> AMI: It's just that I can
honestly say right now I trust
Eliza more than I trust Lisa.
I'm sorry, but I just do.
>> LISA: I want to know why.
>> AMI: Just because Liza has
always been straight up with me.
There are just little things
that have set me off.
>> LISA: You know, you need to
trust me.
You need... you need to trust
me.
>> AMI: Well, honey, then you
need to make me believe that I
can trust you.
>> LISA: Well, I don't know...
You know what?
I'll be honest, Ami, I haven't
done one thing to make you not
trust me except this comment
which I think is unfair.
I think it's unfair.
>> AMI: It's not just...
It's little things, honey.
>> SCOUT: Let it go.
>> AMI: Like your anger building
up towards me isn't helping one
bit, like, and I can feel it.
>> LISA: I'm kind of insulted.
I'm with you, even if it means
Julie and Twila aren't...
>> SCOUT: Here's a Bible.
>> LISA: Oh. Right hand.
I mean, I am.
>> SCOUT: Here's a Bible.
You're with us till the end of
the line.
So you know she's here till the
end.
>> AMI: Yeah.
>> LISA: I swear to you.
I'm here till the end. Swear.
You know what?
I don't need a person I don't
know not trusting me.
I mean, you know what?
For me to sit there and act like
I'm swearing on the Bible.
You know, I'm not doing that
anymore either.
I refuse to do that again.
I'm not going to swear to my God
to please these people who can't
trust me.
I'm not going to do it anymore.
I'm not going to kiss Ami's butt
to stay in this game.
I wish her butt was out of here
right now, to tell you the
truth, because I'm so mad.
>> RORY: You know I adore Lisa.
>> SCOUT: I do, too.
I trust her.
>> RORY: Actually I'd rather
Eliza left, quite frankly.
I'd rather you figure out how to
get those ladies to change their
opinion.
>> SCOUT: Well, if I could get
Lisa to go sit down with Ami
but, um, she won't do it, and
there's a tiff between the two
of them.
>> RORY: Between Lisa and Ami?
>> SCOUT: Yeah.
>> RORY: What's the tiff?
>> SCOUT: Hell if I know.
>> RORY: Amazingly enough, my
name is not going to come up in
Tribal Council today, and I'm
just so ecstatic.
I could care less who I vote
for.
All I want is for someone to
leave the island other than me.
You know, I'm just happy to be
here.
>> AMI: Oh, yeah, I'm happy...
Do you know how happy I am that
you're here?
>> RORY: I am so happy.
>> AMI: What?
>> RORY: I am just happy right
now.
>> AMI: There's no way my ass is
voting for you today.
No way.
>> RORY: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
It's a knockout for the kid!
>> LISA: Sure.
We're ready.
We love Tribal Council.
>> RORY: I'm happy as a pig in a
poke right now.
I'm just... the rat has found a
crack, and that crack has become
a fissure and nobody gave me any
odds to break this alliance of
women, and I have broken it.
>> JEFF: Welcome back to Tribal
Council.
Scout, since you re-divided into
two new tribes you guys have not
won a challenge.
>> SCOUT: Yeah, pitiful, isn't
it?
We've got to quit meeting like
this, Jeff.
>> JEFF: It's easy to get along
when you're winning.
>> SCOUT: Right.
>> JEFF: You guys are in
trouble.
>> SCOUT: Right.
>> JEFF: I mean, you got blown
out again today, and now you
will have fewer members than
Lopevi.
>> SCOUT: You know what, that's
just how it is, but we don't
feel whooped yet.
Our tails are not dragging, and
we're going to keep giving it
the best shot we've got.
>> JEFF: Leann, you had to feel
a little responsible today.
>> LEANN: A lot responsible.
I can only say that I know now
that swimming is not my strong
point (chuckles) and hopefully
I can be an asset in other
challenges, and I don't think
I'm too bad to live with, so I
hope they keep me around.
>> JEFF: Scout, given the
choice of voting out somebody
based on loyalty or based on
strength in helping me in a
challenge, which way do you
lean?
>> SCOUT: I would lean toward
loyalty.
Loyalty is really important.
>> JEFF: Eliza, you think people
can trust you in this tribe?
>> ELIZA: I think that the
people that I've told that they
can trust me, I think they do
trust me, yeah, definitely.
>> RORY: She hasn't told me that
though.
(scattered chuckling)
>> ELIZA: You can trust me,
Rory.
(Rory mutters)
>> JEFF: A little late for that,
huh, Rory?
Lisa, do you think people trust
you at this point?
>> LISA: You know what, I sure
hope so.
I've proven it a couple of
times, and I'm sticking to my
word, Jeff.
I'm sticking to what I've said
and you know what, that's the
only thing I can hope for.
I don't know what else I can do.
>> JEFF: Ami, given the choice,
I'm going to keep somebody
'cause I know I can trust them,
I'm going to keep somebody I'm
not sure about trust, but right
now, I just need them on my
tribe.
>> AMI: Um... loyalty.
I'm going to go with loyalty
right now.
>> JEFF: Rory, where does that
put you?
>> RORY: Jeff, we know where
that puts me.
It put me on the hot spot, and
it's the same hot spot that I've
been all along, but what can I
do?
I mean, my ass is hanging out,
Jeff.
I've worked 110% from day one
that I've been with Yasur, and
all I asked was for a fair
shake.
That's all I've asked for.
>> JEFF: It is time to vote.
Eliza, you're up.
>> LISA: Well, I really don't
want to vote you off, but I want
to prove that my word is good
with the ladies.
Anyway, good luck.
>> SCOUT: Rory, this is not a
vote against you.
This is a vote in support of our
alliance, and it's an honoring
vote for Lisa, who I really
cherish.
I couldn't put her name down.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Lisa.
Rory.
One vote Lisa, one vote Rory.
Two votes Rory, one vote Lisa.
Lisa.
Two votes Lisa, two votes Rory.
Three votes Lisa, two votes
Rory.
The seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu...
Lisa.
You need to bring me your torch.
Lisa, the tribe has spoken.
>> LISA: True to my word.
>> JEFF: The last time you left
here, it was girls sticking
together all the way.
Obviously, after tonight's vote,
that is no longer the case.
As a tribe, you've got some
catching up to do.
Tomorrow is another day.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> JULIE: I just think the guys
are going to shaft us.
>> JEFF: Julie and Twila
conspire.
>> JULIE: But little do they
know.
>> JEFF: And Rory tries to break
into the women's alliance.
>> RORY: I don't know them men.
I know you guys a lot better
than I know them.
>> AMI: You're definitely in a
rough spot right now.
>> RORY: If I get voted off this
island, the Yasur tribe will
burn.
>> LISA: I was voted off because
there were a few women whom I
tried to be trustworthy with,
particularly Ami, and they could
not trust me, for whatever
reason I don't know, but she
definitely had some power over
the other women and so they
voted me out and that's the way
it is, but I believe it was
totally unfair.