>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> I didn't trust you.
>> PROBST: Lisa and Eliza
clashed after Lisa switched
alliances.
>> Now, you can either
take that or not, Eliza.
>> I'm furious.
I'm gonna be civil to her, but
if she were gone tomorrow, I
would be thrilled.
>> PROBST: At Lopevi, John and
Brady felt their days were
numbered.
>> I can't stand the
way that this tribe ended up.
Why are we letting fat dudes run
the show?
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the memory skills of
the Yasur women won them Da, an
island native for 24 hours.
Da is a rock star when it comes
to living on the island.
Back at camp, Da got right to
business, uncovering a bounty of
food for the Yasur women.
>> Good stuff.
>> Oh...
>> Is it sweet?
>> Who knew we had all this
food right in our backyard?
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, the women worked well
under the guidance of Eliza.
>> Okay, yellow skull,
brown skull.
Switch it, switch it, switch it!
>> Brown skull...
>> We got it.
>> PROBST: But Rory failed to
control his tribe.
>> Move that down...
>> Hey, switch like colors.
>> Guys, guys.
>> PROBST: Guys need to work
together, or you're never gonna
solve this.
>> I think we got it, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Yasur wins immunity.
( cheering )
After losing the challenge for
Lopevi, Rory knew he was in
trouble.
>> I hope the five of us
really are together, 'cause if
not...
>> Without a doubt.
>> ...I'm dead right now.
>> PROBST: And Sarge wavered
with the older alliance, giving
John and Brady new hope.
>> If Brady, uh, gets voted
out, I'm gonna lose a real good
work partner.
>> Sarge could, at the
last second, make a change.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Sarge held to his
alliance, and Brady was voted
out.
Brady, the tribe has spoken.
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
( birds singing )
>> Sarge, last night you
were talking about a different
vote we were gonna maybe have
this morning about sleeping.
>> What's that?
>> Did you bring it up?
>> Oh, yeah, some people
were upset, and I said, the
easiest thing to do is just vote
on rotating around the fire.
>> Well, I mean, you're
in the house, so, I mean, what's
it to you?
>> But people were upset
that you sleep in the same spot
every night.
>> Well, they can build
a bridge and get over it.
>> We're a team.
You didn't come here to be an
individualist.
You came here to be a team.
>> But if you had the
problem, Chad, why couldn't you
be man enough to come and tell
me yourself?
>> It's not just me.
>> It wasn't just Chad.
>> Well, then why didn't
you come to me personally?
Why did you have to go to him?
>> We talked about this before.
>> We-we talked about it.
You said build a bridge and get
over it.
>> Everybody thinks that
there's certain spots around the
fire that are better than
others, and I don't think that's
true.
>> Yeah.
>> These two spots are the
worst.
That spot right...
That strip there for two is
like...
is like first class.
Some positions are more
desirable than others, because
the wind comes generally from
one direction, and it blows the
smoke and sparks and ash over
one edge of the fire.
Bubba just would not give up
this prime spot.
>> Where you were last
night, just move one spot over.
It's no big deal.
>> I won't even sleep
around the fire.
>> Oh, Bubba, come on.
>> That's what everybody wants,
bro.
>> Don't do that.
Don't-don't do that, brother.
>> There's a lot of
testosterone in the camp.
It's the little things that are
getting on people's nerves.
I'm kind of getting tired of
hanging out with these men.
( laughs )
It's so lonely.
>> Oh, man, there's dudes
down there in a canoe or
something.
>> It looks like they're
coming this way.
>> It does.
>> If I knew we was
gonna have visitors, I'd have
baked a cake.
>> When the two men
arrived, immediately I was
pretty excited about it.
I mean, it's the first visitor
we've had, and we've not had a
lot of interaction with the nee
Vanuatu.
( speaking native language )
>> One chief.
One chief.
>> The guy came out and
started talking to us in some
language that I have no idea.
The one thing we could kind of
pick out is that he wanted us to
establish a-a leader.
( speaking native language )
>> One chief...
>> Who's chief?
>> I guess he wants
somebody to go with him.
>> Sarge, I think you're
leaving.
>> One chief.
>> They said, "Hey, Sarge,
they're calling for you."
They said "You've got to go with
them."
I got ready to go, and I took my
long pants off and got my socks
off and everything, got ready to
go.
Then all of a sudden, he hands
me a chief staff, and then he
puts the chief, uh, emblem
around my neck.
Then he turns around and gets in
his boat, and we're, like, "I
guess I'm not going with him."
>> What the hell's going
on today?
( speaking native language )
>> One chief.
>> Choose one chief.
>> Choose one chief?
>> Scout.
>> Scout?
>> Scout's our chief.
>> Scout.
She's definitely our chief.
She's the oldest.
She's the wisest.
I think it was obvious for all
of us.
>> That's it?
Uh-oh.
>> Uh-oh.
>> Thank you.
>> Going bye-bye?
>> Have a good day.
Thank you.
>> We're not really sure
what this is all about, but we
kind of have a feeling that the
tribes are going to get mixed up
in some way, but it could be
anything.
How do we know?
We just have to wait and see.
( loud rumbling )
>> Holy...
Oh, my God.
( bats squeaking )
>> Whoa!
Did you feel that earthquake?
( rumbling continues )
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
( loud, thunderous rumbling )
( bats squeaking )
>> I have never...
Whoa.
Still going, bro.
Hey!
>> Hey, hey...
>> Ride 'em, cowboy.
( loud cawing )
>> That scared the daylights
out of me. Whew!
>> We don't have those in
Colorado.
>> I have never felt like
that in my life.
Yeah, I felt the ground opening.
I'm telling you.
>> I mean, I'm like, dude.
I mean, I heard about
earthquakes, but I never
imagined the whole earth just
frickin'...
>> It's still going.
It's going.
>> I loved it.
>> Oh, I'm shaking like a...
Look at my hand.
( laughs )
>> You rock 'n' roll, Mama.
>> Yeah.
I'm happy. Whoo!
>> I could do without that.
>> PROBST: Okay, before we get
to business, did anybody feel
the earthquake?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> That was the wildest
thing of the day.
>> Yes.
>> That was my cherry, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Bubba, that was your
first earthquake?
>> That was my first
earthquake.
At-at first, you could, like,
hear it before you hit, and,
buddy, when it hit, man, them
trees started shaking, coconuts
started falling.
I mean, it was a sight.
Oh, I was excited.
>> PROBST: Yasur, what was going
on when it hit for you guys,
Lisa?
>> Oh.
>> I was, uh, chopping
vegetables, and I'm not kidding,
I thought the ground was getting
ready to split.
It scared the daylights out of
me.
>> PROBST: All right, well,
let's get down to the business
about why chiefs were selected.
Sarge, Scout, over here.
Everybody else, drop your buffs.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: All right.
Let me explain how it's gonna
work.
One of you two is going to
divide these two tribes into two
new tribes, mixing up the men
and the women.
Because there is one extra
woman, one woman will not be
chosen.
We'll deal with that later.
Once the tribes have been
divided, the other leader will
choose which tribe they want to
take back with them to their
beach.
To make things fair, we'll rock,
paper, scissor to see who gets
to divide the tribes and who
gets to choose.
>> One, two, three.
>> PROBST: Paper covers rock.
Sarge, do you want to divide, or
do you want to choose?
>> I'll choose.
>> PROBST: It's on you.
You're gonna divide these
tribes.
Make sure you divide them as
evenly as possible, alternating
between men and women to make
sure it doesn't hurt you later
when Sarge chooses which tribe
he wants.
>> Rory.
>> PROBST: Now pick another guy
to go to the other tribe.
>> Chad.
>> PROBST: Scout, pick one woman
to join Rory.
>> Eliza.
>> PROBST: Eliza joins Rory.
Pick a woman to join Chad.
>> Jules.
>> PROBST: Julie joins Chad.
Pick another guy to join Rory
and Eliza.
>> Bubba.
>> PROBST: Pick another guy to
join Chad and Julie.
>> Chris.
>> PROBST: Chris says hello to
Chad.
Scout, pick a woman to join
Eliza, Bubba and Rory.
>> Leann.
>> Hello.
>> PROBST: Pick a woman to join
Julie, Chad and Chris.
>> Twila.
>> PROBST: All right.
John is the last man.
Tell John where he's going.
>> With, uh, Chad and
Chris and Jules and Twila.
>> PROBST: Now we're down to a
really tough decision.
Two women left.
One woman is going to join
Bubba, Leann, Eliza and Rory.
Which one is it going to be?
>> Ami.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Scout has divided the tribes.
Sarge, which group do you want
to take back with you to Lopevi?
Go join 'em.
Scout, go join your new Yasur
tribe.
Yasur, Yasur.
Drop yours, Sarge.
Everybody's getting a new buff.
It's a new Lopevi tribe.
All right.
Lisa, because you
were not chosen...
>> I'm going bye-bye?
>> PROBST: You get to choose.
>> Yes!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
>> Come on, try something easy.
>> Come on, Lisa.
>> PROBST: Take your time.
>> We need you, Lis.
>> We want you, Lisa.
>> Lunch is ready when you
get back.
>> We really want you, Lisa.
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
All right!
( Yasur cheering )
>> Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
Yes!
Thank you so much!
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
your first challenge as new
tribes.
It is for reward.
Here's how it works.
One tribe member at a time is
going to dive off the platform,
swim out to a buoy, dive down,
retrieve a marker.
There are 13 markers in total.
Deepest marker is 30 feet down.
The deeper you go, the harder it
gets.
Bring it back to the platform
and get it up on the board.
This is timed game.
After ten minutes, whichever
tribe has the most wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> ALL: Yeah.
>> PROBST: Been out here a
while.
Little bit of a shakeup.
Figured your taste buds could
use...
>> Oh, Jeff...
>> PROBST: Pringles and beer.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: Give you a little
tease.
You get one chip for the tribe.
>> All right!
>> We only get one chip?
>> PROBST: That's it.
>> Oh, Jeff.
>> Cheers.
>> Here we go.
>> Mm.
Oh, my lord.
>> PROBST: Okay.
For the winning
tribe, you will leave here.
You'll be taken to a waterfall.
All the Pringles, all the beer
you can put down your gut.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Yasur, you have one
extra member.
You're sitting somebody out.
Who's sitting out?
>> Bubba.
>> PROBST: Bubba's going to sit
this one out.
Everybody else swim out, wait
for my go.
Here we go, for reward: a day
at the waterfalls, Pringles and
beer.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Here we go.
>> PROBST: Scout and Twila first
out.
Twila first down.
Scout trailing.
Twila can't get it untied,
coming up for air.
Scout's been underwater a long
time.
>> Scout!
>> PROBST: Scout has the first
marker for Yasur.
>> Come back.
>> Come on back.
>> PROBST: Twila can't get a
marker, coming back.
Yasur with one marker.
Chad in the water.
Leann in the water.
Chad has it.
Chad back with Lopevi's first
marker.
Got to get up on the board.
Go.
Julie going down to eight feet.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Leann has the eight-
foot marker.
>> Good job, Yasur!
>> PROBST: Yasur up 2-1.
Julie's been down there a long
time, and she has it.
Rory heading down to 10 feet.
Lopevi, good to go.
Rory's yanking on something.
He's got it.
Sarge has his.
We're dead even.
Yasur with three.
Good to go.
Lopevi with three.
Chris is heading to 12 feet.
Eliza back with one for Yasur.
>> Way to go, Yasur!
>> PROBST: Yasur leads...
>> ( grunts ): I dropped it.
>> Oh, shoot.
>> You dropped it?
>> What happens if he dropped it
it?
>> PROBST: Chris lost his
marker.
It's gone.
You got to get the next one.
Chris has lost one marker for
Lopevi.
Five minutes left.
John going down for Lopevi.
Ami heading in for Yasur.
Yasur up 4-3.
John ties it up.
4-4.
John heading back out for
another marker.
Both guys under a long time.
Ami with another marker.
John with another marker.
Yasur with five.
Lopevi with five.
John's worn out.
>> Here we go.
>> PROBST: Julie got another
marker for Lopevi.
Rory ties it up.
6-6.
Three minutes left.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Chris with the
seventh marker.
( Yasur cheering )
Ami back with another one for
Yasur.
Tied up 7-7.
>> ( screams )
>> PROBST: Sarge trying, can't
get it.
>> It's unbearable.
My ears.
>> You got to come back or go
down.
>> Oh, he got it.
>> PROBST: Yasur leads 8-7.
We're down to two minutes.
John heads down to 22 feet.
Yasur has eight.
Lopevi has seven.
John!
We're tied at eight.
Both tribes tied at eight.
Less than a minute left.
Next marker that comes up will
have the lead.
Both have been under a long
time.
>> Come on, Ami.
>> PROBST: Chris really working
it.
>> That thing is deep.
And I got it!
( Lopevi cheering )
>> PROBST: Lopevi in the lead.
It's up to Ami.
If she's comes up with a marker,
Yasur ties.
If she doesn't, Lopevi wins.
Amy can't do it.
We're out of time.
Lopevi wins reward.
All the Pringles and beer at a
waterfall.
Amazing effort, guys.
Yasur, you have a new tribe, and
for some of you, a new home.
Head on back to shore.
Lopevi, congratulations on your
first win as a new tribe.
>> ALL: Yeah!
>> PROBST: You will leave from
here.
You'll head directly to the
waterfalls.
All the Pringles you can eat,
all the beer you can drink.
Good chance to get to know each
other.
Head on in.
>> Yeah!
>> Different flavors, guys.
>> Different flavors!
>> Yeah!
>> Ice-cold beer.
>> I like original.
>> After spending 11 days
eating greens and plantains,
this tastes like gold.
>> Great job today, guys.
>> Let's do it.
( all cheering )
>> Ow!
>> We got our new buffs,
our new tribe mates.
We got rid of some people, and
now, um, it seems like
everybody's kind of happy.
>> Oh, man, this tastes good!
>> Ow!
>> And summer's great!
Yeah, you got the summer.
>> Awesome!
I can relate to this guy.
I'm loving this.
I've got something to talk
about. Yes!
I love my other tribe.
Am I going to miss 'em?
Oh, hell, yes.
But yet I fit in better with
these guys up here.
I'm already kicking with these
guys where I was never able to
kick with the girls.
Do you take yours in comp when
you get overtime?
>> Yeah, oh, yeah.
I max out every year.
>> That is wild, dude!
Another guy that works for
highway transportation.
You know, this is just, you
know... things are clicking.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Doesn't this feel...?
>> Oh, yeah, the mist is
awesome.
>> I'm all buzzed up.
I mean, not from the beer, but
just buzzed up from the change
and, you know, the evolution
here.
I'm sure there's underlying
things going on, you know.
I mean, two women, the rest of
the men, so are they going to
try to pick us off?
I don't know, so me and Twila
are trying to weasel our way in
there pretty tight.
>> As soon as the
tribes started to swap, I was
psyched, because I knew that my
odds in this game had
drastically increased.
I was starting to get scared
because the guys' alliance was
really tight, and I wasn't a
member of it.
But the bottom line is now that
it's broken up, that's all the
work that I was trying to do is
break it up.
I'm just psyched.
I mean, our tribe's looking
really good.
Compared to the other tribe, I
think we really have an
advantage.
>> We had a tribe swap of
sorts today.
>> Welcome to our shack.
>> We lost the reward
challenge, which was
disappointing, but, you know, we
don't even feel the loss right
now, because everyone's kind of
excited that there are new faces
around.
>> Vittles on.
>> Thanks.
>> Go ahead.
Isn't too bad, huh, guys?
>> Thank you, ladies, so much.
>> Yeah, you're making
us feel very welcome.
>> Well, you're part of
our tribe now.
>> I thought it'd feel
kind of strange, but this is all
right.
That's the best meal I've had
since I've been here.
By far.
>> We have sugar cane, by
the way.
>> Get out!
>> We've been chewing
sticks of sugar.
>> I've been dying for
sugared stuff.
I think I'm really going to
enjoy living over here with the
ladies, and stuff like that.
>> You're not going to
swallow it.
>> You chew it.
Chew it and spit it out.
>> Being in a tribe with
a bunch of women, it does make
you nervous, because one wrong
move, buddy, and they'll vote
you out.
Don't think they won't.
I guess you could say I'm
sweating like a prostitute in
church, I guess you could say.
( laughing )
>> Wiggle, wiggle.
There you go.
You're the man.
These guys right now seem pretty
willing to please.
Right now they're just like
whatever it takes to get it
done.
>> We going to show them
how to do the coconut?
Hey, did y'all see how...?
>> Why?
>> Huh?
>> Why what?
We've been showing the guys all
kinds of stuff, and I said,
"Oh, I'm going to show them how
to crack the coconut."
Ami was, like, "Why?"
Because to show them how to do
it-- it's cool.
Well, why would you want to do
that?
You know, I'm like...
why not?
>> You want to teach them,
teach them.
>> I think it's kind of
cool.
>> I was so happy that Rory
and Bubba started lifting stuff
and moving stuff and doing
stuff.
What I got irritated with was I
saw a little bit of our bond
disappear.
The girls were so excited to
show them everything.
I just don't think it's really
that important that we show them
all of our secrets.
We're definitely still five
women strong.
That's not going to change; at
least on my end it's not going
to change.
I'm sticking by the ladies.
So, they really need to prove
themselves.
Otherwise, they're out of here.
There we go.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
today's immunity challenge.
First things first.
Scout.
>> Chris, think about
the merge.
>> PROBST: Immunity-- back up
for grabs.
Let me explain how it's going to
work.
You're going to race into the
jungle, collecting pieces to
build an outrigger canoe.
Both tribes will start with your
canoe on the beach.
Two tribe members will go into
the jungle, untie the frame,
bring it back.
The next two tribe members will
go deeper into the jungle, untie
two paddles, bring them back.
The last two tribe members will
go even further into the jungle,
untie the outrigger, bring it
back.
Once you've gathered all the
pieces on the beach, you can
begin to assemble the outrigger.
Two tribe members will then
paddle out, retrieve the tribe
flag, come back to the beach.
Your outrigger must hit the
final marker pole on your way
back.
First tribe with all six tribe
members and their tribe flag on
the mat wins immunity.
The losers-- Tribal Council, and
this game will be over tonight
for somebody.
Yasur, you have one extra tribe
member, got to sit somebody out.
Bubba sat out yesterday.
Who's sitting out today?
>> I'll sit out.
>> PROBST: Scout, you're going
to sit this one out.
Everybody else take your spots,
wait for my go.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Sarge and Twila attacking the
knots.
Bubba with the first knot
undone.
>> Pull, pull, pull it out.
You got to start pulling the
other one.
>> PROBST: One knot left in the
center; Twila working on that.
Dead even.
Lopevi has their frame.
>> Bring it down here,
Sarge!
>> PROBST: Yasur right behind.
Bubba taking it all.
>> Pick it up.
Come on, go, go!
>> Hit the mat, hit the
mat.
Ami, you hit the mat, too.
>> PROBST: Next two-- go, go,
go!
Chad and Julie with a bit of a
head start on the paddles.
Leann and Eliza right behind.
>> Come on, let's get those
oars back!
>> PROBST: Julie, almost there.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Yasur, making up a
lot of time.
Leann has hers free.
She's helping Eliza.
We're dead even.
Chad and Julie are out.
Leann and Eliza right behind.
>> Come on, ladies, let's go!
>> Come on, Julie, come on!
>> Get ready.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Next two-- go!
Leann and Eliza right behind.
Yasur's still in it.
Next two-- go!
Final piece.
>> Come on, dude.
>> PROBST: John working his
knots.
Rory right behind working on
his.
John with a bit of a lead.
Rory trying to make up some
ground.
Still very tight.
John getting very close.
Rory falling a bit behind.
Rory going to have to make up a
lot of ground for Yasur.
>> Do it.
>> PROBST: John very close.
>> Lower it down, okay?
As soon as my end touches the
ground, come on down.
>> PROBST: Chris and John
getting the outrigger portion.
Chris untying the last knot.
John and Chris have the
outrigger.
They're heading back to the
beach.
>> Steady pace; I'm right
behind you.
>> PROBST: Yasur losing a lot of
time.
>> Pace, pace, pace.
>> They are not even close.
>> PROBST: Go, Rory, you're in
this.
Lopevi still needs to assemble
their canoe.
>> Hey, Chad, ready?
>> On the side.
>> Start assembling.
>> Over, in.
>> I got it.
>> PROBST: Lopevi with a big
lead.
>> Come on, Rory!
>> Come on, let's go.
>> PROBST: Rory's dragging it.
A lot of ground to make up.
Start assembling.
Ooh, careful.
>> Watch out, watch out, watch
out.
JEFF: Both tribes working on
their outriggers.
Lopevi with a big lead.
Lisa working for Yasur, Bubba
working for Yasur, Yasur working
very well together, making up
some time.
Lopevi has theirs together.
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Get in.
Get in, Chad.
We can't go no farther.
>> Go; push the other
way, Chad.
I'll turn it, I'll turn it;
we're fine.
Keep pushing, Chad.
>> PROBST: Chad and John working
together out to retrieve the
tribe flag.
The big lead on Yasur.
>> You ready?
>> PROBST: Get out there.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Yasur in the water.
>> Get in, Bubba.
>> Go.
Head the right direction.
>> PROBST: Yasur with a terrible
push-off.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: They pushed their
tribe completely the wrong
direction.
>> We're going backwards.
>> PROBST: Panic by Yasur in a
bad push-off.
>> Turn it around.
>> PROBST: Let's go, Yasur.
Pick it up.
>> We've got to go from
that side, all right?
>> Straighten it out.
>> Don't worry, man,
just paddle!
>> PROBST: Lopevi's now all over
the map.
>> Go, go!
>> Stroke, stroke.
>> Grab it, Chad!
There you go.
Yeah!
>> PROBST: Lopevi has their
tribe flag.
Yasur's closing the gap.
>> Keep it going!
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Yasur with their
tribe flag.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: They're around the
buoy and heading back.
>> Row!
>> PROBST: Going to be a race to
the finish.
>> Paddle the other
side, bro.
When you paddle that way, it
turns, man.
>> PROBST: Lopevi heading the
wrong way.
>> Oh, whoa.
>> PROBST: Yasur's still in
this.
>> Chad, use the bottom
to turn, use the bottom to turn!
>> PROBST: Lopevi's got to hit
their flag.
>> Get out, get out, get out!
>> PROBST: Lopevi wins immunity!
( cheering )
Lopevi-- congratulations.
Nobody going home tonight.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> PROBST: Yasur, not sure what
went on out there.
Rory, you lost a lot of time on
the knots.
Some of the worst paddling I've
ever seen.
Somebody's going to pay for it
tonight.
See you at Tribal Council.
Head back to camp.
>> Tribal Council is coming up
and Bubba and I are both...
it's very, very apparent
that one of the two of us has
got to go.
I feel the women of Yasur are
going to vote as a solid block.
I feel extremely vulnerable.
The only thing I can do is
assume the worst and hope for
the best and pray to God that
I'm here tomorrow.
>> What did we look like
out there?
Did we look like total idiots,
or what?
I'm annoyed as hell with Bubba
right now.
The second that we arrived at
our challenge, I see Bubba
making signals to Chris.
He was communicating completely,
and Chris was nodding like,
"Yep, that's right.
Yep, that's right."
Bubba was not helping me one
bit.
>> No.
>> During the entire time,
I...
>> Was he trying to tell...
>> Yes.
I saw him talking to Chris.
I just watched it happen the
whole time.
It was disgusting.
People will...
people will get
themselves kicked out.
You don't have kick them out.
They'll get themselves kicked
out.
I don't know exactly how the
other girls are voting, but I
definitely have my vote.
Bubba is not part of the tribe.
He's making plans with the other
team.
That's...
Can you see Michael Jordan
whispering over to the other
team what their next play is?
Hell, no.
He is not on our team.
He's out.
I'm done with him.
>> What do you guys want
to eat?
>> When we got to the
immunity challenge and I saw my
old tribe mates, out of a-a
desperate chance, trying to
communicate with Chris, I was
trying to mouth "merge" for
him to think of the merge.
Because if, uh, they win all
these immunity challenges, the
women are going to have the
advantage during the merge, and
they're going to pick the guys
off one by one.
But, who knows, I may have got
caught with my hands in the
cookie jar.
>> Losing sure does take it
out of you.
>> It took the wind out
of my sails.
If y'all choose me, will you
tell me before I go?
>> I don't know.
You have to ask the boss.
>> I just said, "If you
choose...
could you tell me
before I go?"
>> Ask everybody, you'll find...
everyone knows.
>> I didn't...
I didn't say that.
I just said if y'all choose I'd
like to know before I go.
I just don't want to get
blindsided, you know what I'm
saying?
You know, that's all I ask.
I wasn't asking for you to vote
either way.
I just would like to know.
>> Yeah, no, I hear you.
>> Ami noticed Bubba
making, uh, hand signals and
working with the other team
trying to signal them something,
so, how do you feel about that,
little one?
>> I'm worried that we're
shooting ourselves in the
foot, you know.
>> Yeah.
>> I just think it's
going to be...
I just think it's
going to get harder.
I don't know.
>> Okay.
>> It's definitely
dangerous to vote the guys off.
These challenges are going to be
physical and we are going to
need their strength.
I don't want to vote off Bubba
or Rory.
We like them both a lot.
I think we could...
potentially,
like, we're already down four
guys to two.
Now we're going to be down to
just one guy on our team and
then we're going to have really
physical challenges and...
What?
>> We're not going to kick
one of us off.
>> Thank you, Lord, for
everything that you've done for
us.
Thank you for all the
opportunities that you've given
us and thank you for the
beautiful days on Vanuatu.
Thank you, Lord, thank you.
Amen.
You know I love you, brother.
>> I love you, too, bro.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Tribal
Council.
Let's go back to when we
switched.
Lisa, after being women and men
this long, is this truly one
new tribe now?
>> Well, we've tried to
make them as welcome in the
tribe, and we actually have
enjoyed having two men around.
Feels like they have been with
us forever, and I've personally
enjoyed it a lot.
>> PROBST: Leann, what's the
reaction on a split?
Is it, "All right, this is the
tribe I'm on now and who knows
what's coming next?"
>> I think it's really
difficult after 11 days of
bonding with all these women,
and I'm not going to lie, I
haven't made the switch.
>> PROBST: So it's still men
versus women for you?
>> Yes, it is.
>> PROBST: Ami, are they equal
members, even though there are
five women and two men?
>> This morning I thought
we were one team.
I was excited about the
challenge.
I was ready to go, and I see
Bubba making signals to Chris,
and the second I saw that
signal, I'm like, we're not a
team; this is not a team here.
That... I-I saw it happen.
>> PROBST: So, Bubba, at today's
immunity challenge, you tried to
get a signal or you gave a
signal?
>> I was trying to get a
signal to let me know if they
were going to play it to win or
they were going to strategize
trying to get more men into
the merge.
>> PROBST: What were you hoping
to get back?
>> Just a...
a thumbs up
or a smile or a wave--
something.
I took a chance.
It was a big gamble.
>> We had all intentions
on winning.
>> And you weren't going to
be the one that we had picked,
if we did lose, to go.
>> PROBST: Rory, a little
worried on your end, then?
>> The fact of the matter
is, Jeff, the only thing that
could have changed our fate is
for Yasur to have won immunity
today.
That's the only thing that was
going to stop one of us two from
leaving tonight.
>> PROBST: Ami, is it a little
difficult for you to know you're
going to sacrifice both these
guys when they really didn't do
anything other than end up on
the wrong end of the buff?
>> Yeah, it's a little
difficult for me, but I'm glad--
sorry to say this, guys-- but
I'm glad that we have them and
it's not Twila or Jules that are
going home tonight.
>> PROBST: Bubba, so why should
they keep you?
>> Because I-I busted my
butt trying to win.
I almost drowned when I was a
kid in the ocean.
I never set foot in the ocean
till I got here.
Six weeks I came here, I learned
how to swim.
So you know me getting my butt
in that boat was making a big
step, so I am a team player.
It's just, I made a mistake.
If you need to win challenges
and stuff, you know beyond a
shadow of a doubt, I'm going to
bust my butt to do it.
>> PROBST: Rory, why Bubba and
not you?
>> These women know where
my heart is, and they know that
if anybody is capable of being
110% part of this team, it's
me.
I go down with my ship, and if I
can't break into that union of
women, of the sisters, then I'm
going to take my lumps.
I'm man enough to do that.
>> I just wanted to say
when I...
initially divided up
the teams, there were three guys
that I really wanted to play the
game with, and these are two of
them, and, uh, the game ain't
over till the fat lady sings.
>> PROBST: It is time to vote.
Leann, you're up.
>> Bubba, you know you're
my brother.
We were just put in an awkward
situation where it was going to
be you or I.
>> Rory, I picked you,
and, uh, go get him, girls.
>> Sorry, Bubba, you know
why.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Travis-- Bubba.
Rory.
One vote Bubba, one vote Rory.
Bubba.
That's two Bubba.
That's three votes Bubba.
The sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu...
Bubba.
That's four votes.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Bubba, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Peace out, y'all.
>> PROBST: Well, Yasur is now
down to six members, same number
as Lopevi.
The question is, will the women
stay united?
Will there be a merge?
A lot of questions, a lot of
game left.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> I will not...
>> PROBST: Rory makes a daring
move.
>> ...continue to slave
around camp if I do not have a
shot at making it through Tribal
Council.
My speech was so cheesy, I
couldn't even believe I was
saying it.
>> PROBST: And the clothes come
off at Lopevi.
>> I think the coed thing
is working really well for our
tribe now.
>> I had a great time
playing.
Got in trouble throwing a little
signal.
I think the Yankees are going to
give me a job to work first base
so I can send some signals.
It really shocked me how close
you can become with a person
when you're with them that long.
And one thing I learned, the
important thing is what you have
in life and that's my family.