>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Survivors, ready?
Go!
The tribe competed as two
randomly split teams of four.
Chris, Chad and Ami dragged
Eliza across the finish line
first.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: The four embarked on
a cultural experience of a
lifetime...
(men singing)
...and were treated to an array
of Vanuatu customs.
(Chad gags, coughs)
Back at camp, the others endured
a terrible storm.
>> It's going to be a miracle
if we can keep our fire.
I've never been in a worse
situation than this.
>> PROBST: The next morning,
Scout proposed a plan to first
oust Eliza and then Ami.
When the others returned from
the reward, Ami suspected
something was up.
>> I had really weird feelings.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Chad and Twila hung
in the longest.
And Chad is slipping.
>> Go down, Chad, go
down.
>> PROBST: Twila wins immunity.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Back at camp, Ami
swayed Leann and Julie to vote
out Chad instead of Eliza...
>> Scout?
>> Yeah?
>> They're not going to
vote for Eliza.
>> PROBST: ...forcing Scout and
Twila to make a tough decision.
>> I'm not going to do
nothing yet.
I'm still thinking.
I'm aggravated.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Scout admitted to scheming with
the guys.
>> We have talked quite a
bit about different strategies
to get to the end of the game.
>> It makes me nervous
that two women might be voting
with the two men.
>> PROBST: Although Eliza
received two votes, the women's
alliance held strong, and Chad
was voted out of the tribe...
Chad, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving Chris as the last man
standing.
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
(deep rumbling)
>> I really thought I was
going home, though.
Tribal Council sucks.
I hate it.
I always think I'm going home.
It's kind of funny, but everyone
who conspires against me ends up
off and I'm still here.
>> Yeah.
Scout and Twila come to me and
Chad wanting to form an alliance
with us.
And Scout thought she could get
you and Leann to vote for Eliza.
And when Eliza was gone, then
Scout, Twila, me and Chad would
have the numbers on you, Ami and
Leann, and we'd get rid of Ami
first.
Swear to God on my family's
lives.
As soon as I got back to camp, I
narc'd out Scout and Twila, and
I let them know that they had
conspired with me and Chad for
an alliance.
I just, you know, I just mixed
things up as soon as we got
back.
It's going to be a mess.
>> Oh, boy.
This kind of changes everything
in my head for the moment.
>> Mm-hmm.
It's hard to choose what to
believe because it would do
Chris a lot of good to get us
mad at Twila and Scout.
It would make him last longer in
the game.
>> I'm actually very surprised
that things happened the way
they did last night.
So I told Twila about it.
I heard some things that I'm not
very comfortable with, and we
need to talk about it.
>> Paranoia sets in on a
lot of us.
And I think it needs to quit.
>> I have to tell you,
Twila, you're striking me as a
panic player right now.
>> Why?
>> It makes me feel like
you're going to jump ship.
>> She just completely
confirmed the story, but she
told me it was all Scout's idea.
Man, I just didn't think it
would happen this soon.
I thought we'd at least wait
until the guys were gone before
the girls started going crazy on
each other.
But, oh, it's happening.
If they were going to go with
that plan, they should have
stuck with it, 'cause now,
they're screwed.
>> PROBST: And then there were
seven.
All right.
For today's challenge, we're
going to test how much you
recall from the past 28 days.
I'm going to ask you five
questions about past challenges.
Each time you get an answer
right, you score a point.
At the end of five questions,
the person with the most points
wins the reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> Sure do.
>> PROBST: It's no big secret,
after 28 days, the one thing you
miss more than food...
>> Oh, no.
>> No.
>> PROBST: Is love.
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: So here's what we've
set up.
We brought in a satellite.
We have a computer hooked up to
the Internet.
The winner's going to get a
one-hour real-time e-mail
back-and-forth chat.
You can type something, they can
type back to you.
So this is a chance to get
caught up with what's going on
back home, give a little love
and certainly get a whole lot of
love that you need to make it
through the last 11 days.
Worth playing for?
>> ALL: Yeah.
>> PROBST: I want to whet your
appetite and give everybody a
one-minute e-mail hello.
>> Oh, thank God.
Thank you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Let's head in the
hut.
>> Oh, my God!
(laughs)
Oh, my God...
>> PROBST: Twila, you're already
crying.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Well then, let's put
you first. Sit on down.
>> Can somebody else type
for me?
I don't know how to type.
>> PROBST: You don't?
>> No.
>> PROBST: So you don't use
computers much?
>> No.
>> PROBST: No.
You get a... aw...
It's a darn good thing that
we have a camera so you can
hear and see your loved ones.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Hold on here, let's
see if we've got James down
here, your son.
>> Hi. Hi, Mom, how are you?
>> I was being tough
till I seen you.
>> Oh, you're still tough.
We love you.
We miss you a ton.
>> I love you too, buddy.
I miss you so much.
>> PROBST: All right, Twila, you
gotta say your good-byes.
>> I gotta say good-bye,
buddy.
You know I ain't very good at
this dumb stuff, but hope
I get to talk to you later.
>> Do good for me.
>> All right, babe.
>> Love you.
>> Love you, too.
>> Bye.
(Twila sobbing)
>> PROBST: All right, Leann,
have a seat.
>> Oh, boy.
>> PROBST: Let's see who it is.
>> (gasps): Teri!
>> Oh, my God.
>> Hi!
I love you.
I miss you.
>> I love you, too.
I know; I wish I could give you
a big hug.
>> Me, too.
Bye, baby.
>> I love you. Bye.
>> PROBST: Eliza, have a seat.
Who would you most like to talk
to?
>> My mommy.
(squeals) Mommy!
>> PROBST: There she is.
>> I love you, baby.
You're the best.
(kisses)
I wish I could give you a great
big hug; and I miss you
so much, sweetheart.
Be nice to my Lizie out
there, you guys.
>> You heard her.
>> PROBST: Julie.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Have a seat.
Here's Justin.
>> Oh, this is my good friend.
Holy ...
(laughing)
What's up?!
Can you believe this?
>> What's going on?
>> Don't be so relaxed.
Dude... dude!
(laughing)
All right, I miss you.
>> I miss you.
>> All right.
Take care of yourself.
>> I'll see you real
soon, all right?
>> All right, bye-bye.
>> PROBST: Scout.
>> Oh, Scout.
>> PROBST: Let's see if we can't
get your partner up here.
What's her name?
>> Annie.
>> PROBST: There she is.
>> Oh, honey.
Hi... hi, honey.
I love you so much.
>> Oh.
>> I've got my arms wrapped you
all the time.
You know they're there.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: Ami, have a seat.
There can only be one person
you want to talk to.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Who is it?
>> Crissy.
>> PROBST: Who's Crissy?
>> My girlfriend.
>> PROBST: There she is.
>> Hi, baby.
>> It's so good to see your
face.
>> I know, God.
It seems like forever.
I miss you a lot.
>> I miss you a lot, too.
>> No crying.
I love you so much, babe.
I want to go do the best
I can.
>> Yeah, because you get to talk
to me, so do well.
>> I love you.
I'll see you soon.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: That's it.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: Chris.
Who do you want to talk to most?
Would be that be your woman?
Let's see if we can get her up
here.
>> Hi.
>> How you doing?
>> Good; how are you?
>> I'm hanging in there.
>> Put your hands on the screen.
>> I'm right here.
>> It's hard being away
from you, too, baby.
>> Okay.
>> I love you.
>> Oh, I love you, too.
So what kind of plans have
you made for Cancun?
They all already know.
>> Yes, we're gonna get married.
(cheering and applause)
>> PROBST: Wait, I missed that.
>> They're getting married.
>> Congratulations.
>> You're beautiful
and I'll see you soon.
(warm laughter)
>> PROBST: All right.
Shall we do the challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Let's do it.
Take a seat on the bench.
Anywhere is fine.
At stake, a one-hour chat with
your loved one.
Here's how it's going to work.
I'm gonna ask you five questions
about previous challenges.
At the end of five questions,
the person with the most points
wins the reward.
Shall we get started?
>> Sure.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First question:
In the seventh immunity
challenge, who broke the most
tiles with a slingshot, overall?
All right.
Reveal.
The correct answer is Rory,
and everybody has it right.
Everybody's on the board.
Next question: In the "Great
Escape" challenge, who was the
first man to begin assembling
his ladder?
Reveal.
The correct answer was Chad.
Everybody got it right.
We're all tied at two.
Next question: In the second
immunity challenge, where tribes
paired up to collect puzzle
pieces while blindfolded, who
sat out?
Who did not participate in that
challenge?
Everybody reveal.
The correct answer was... Dolly.
Scout got it right.
Leann got it right.
Ami got it right.
Julie got it right.
Eliza got it right.
Here's where we stand: Eliza,
Julie, Leann, Scout, and Ami at
three.
Twila and Chris at two.
Next question: In the fourth
immunity challenge, there were
four different symbols used on
the colored tiles.
Each correct symbol you identify
is worth one point.
Everybody reveal.
The four symbols were the
volcano, the pig head, the
coconut tree or the palm tree,
and a skull.
Chris, pig head is right.
You have one.
Scout, volcano is right, coconut
tree is right, pig is right.
Leann has volcano, pig and palm
tree.
All three are correct.
Ami has volcano, skull, and palm
tree.
Julie: pig, volcano and skull.
You score three.
Eliza has volcano, palm tree and
pig.
You score three.
>> I hate to see that.
>> PROBST: Twila: fish, turtle,
snail and hog.
I'll give you one for the pig.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Here's where we
stand: Chris and Twila at three.
Everybody else tied at six.
Final question: In the first
reward challenge, which survivor
fell into the water the most?
Everybody reveal.
The correct answer was John K.
Chris got it right.
Julie got it right.
Eliza got it right and Twila got
it right.
Julie and Eliza tied at seven
will now go into a tie-breaker
for just those two.
Julie and Ami, switch seats.
At stake, a visit with your
loved one.
In the third reward challenge,
the memory game, name the
matching pairs of items gathered
by the tribes.
The person who gets the most
wins.
These are the items you guys
gathered in the memory game.
Julie has an absolutely blank
look on her face.
Eliza writing like crazy.
Four, three, two, one.
Reveal.
Julie has absolutely nothing
written down.
Which means if Eliza has even
just one right, she wins.
First answer is grapefruit.
"Grapefruit" is right.
You win reward.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Nice job.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Eliza, ready to go
have a little chat with your
mom?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Or would you rather
your mom came out here and
chatted with you?
>> No! Are you kidding!
>> PROBST: Come on out, Susan.
(both shrieking)
>> Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
I can't believe you're here!
I can't believe this!
>> You look so beautiful.
>> Oh, my God!
>> You did it!
>> PROBST: Okay, Susan, here's
the twist.
It's not a one-hour chat.
It's an overnight chat.
Go over and have a seat with
Eliza and get to know everybody.
So you probably figured out
everybody has been here.
We've created a little studio so
you could talk to them.
There's a winner and a bunch of
losers, but because I saw how
much it meant to you guys in
there, you get one little
good-bye.
So Twila, here's your son James.
>> Oh, my God.
My fella!
>> Mom!
>> I miss you so much, so
much, so much, so much.
>> PROBST: Twila, get a good
last hug in.
>> I miss you so much.
>> I love you.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: James, you can have a
spot right here.
All right, Leann, get over here.
Let's get Teri out here.
Come on, Teri.
>> A couple weeks, okay?
I love you.
>> You look awesome.
I love you, too.
Okay, bye.
>> PROBST: Scout, come on over
here.
See if we can rustle up Annie.
(Annie shrieking)
>> Oh, my God.
>> I missed you so much.
Still do.
You look great.
Have fun.
>> PROBST: Julie, let's bring
out Justin.
(Julie shrieking, laughing)
>> My pants are up.
Come here, buddy!
I want to eat you up.
>> PROBST: All right, Ami.
Come on up.
See if Crissy is back there.
Come on out, Crissy.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Hi, baby.
It's so good to hug you again.
>> How about you and I go
over there?
>> PROBST: Chris, come on out
here.
Come on, Laurie.
>> Okay.
Love you, too.
>> PROBST: All right, everybody.
I hate to break this party up.
Your boat has arrived.
You're heading back to the
States.
Say good-bye.
>> Okay, babe.
Okay. Bye.
>> PROBST: All right.
With that, you are going to get
to camp for the night.
They'll take you back and show
you what life on Survivor is
like.
All right, guys, get your stuff,
head back to camp.
Have a good night.
>> I want to hear about
the outside world.
>> Me, too.
>> I'm so glad you're here.
I'm so glad.
Oh, I couldn't be more excited
to be able to share this
experience with my mom.
I want to share everything with
my mom.
My mom is my best friend in the
entire world and I could not be
more excited that she's here
with us.
Oh, Mom, we have leftover trail
mix.
It's just fried coconuts and
plantains.
>> Really?
>> If you want to try.
>> Is it safe for me to get it?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I don't double dip,
even if I'm here.
>> Mom, you don't have a
choice here.
>> Does she look different
to you?
Does she look thinner?
>> She looks thinner.
I know on the, on the computer
screen, her face looks, you
know... bony.
I-I was really worried about
Eliza just being out here.
I was worried about bug bites.
I was worried about parasites.
I was worried that she wouldn't
be flossing every day.
I was worried about Ebola virus.
I was worried about all these
things in the sea, the-the-the
coral and the things that can
cut you and the fish that can
bite you, and...
I was worried.
I don't know how good my letter
was.
>> Your letter was great.
It was fine.
There's definitely a possibility
that people are very resentful
that I won that challenge and
they didn't.
It could definitely work to my
disadvantage, but hopefully, if
she bonds with them, that could
help me.
It was supposed to be me or
Leann gone on day six.
The first time the women lost,
it was either Eliza or Leann,
and it was all-- You want to
know why it was?
What their reasoning was?
I talked too much.
>> You're too annoying.
>> Answer me this.
This morning I asked Twila, I
said, did you, Scout, Chad and
Chris have a plan to vote off
Eliza and then Ami next, and she
said, "That was Scout's idea."
>> Yeah, it was Chad's.
>> That's what she told me.
>> She said it was your plan.
She said it was Scout's idea.
>> And I was like, "What?"
>> When I came out here,
I was determined to play the
game with integrity and honesty
and truth, and if they that
didn't work, then I'd lie, cheat
and steal.
We've now reduced ourselves to
the lie, cheat and steal part.
It was Chad's idea, and that is
the God's honest truth.
Didn't we have an agreement when
we came over here, no matter
what anybody says, we're gonna
stick together.
>> I said we'd stick together
when we came over, but I never
made any promises about
Final Four with you, Scout.
>> Well, I thought you had.
I thought that the three of us
plus Twila, that we would, that
we would go to the...
>> We didn't ever say
anything about the Final Four.
>> So I did a little
damage control there.
But Leann and Ami have backed
out of their alliance with me,
that we would go all the way to
the end of the game together.
Call it Final Four, call it
whatever you want to, we would
go to the end of the game
together and include Twila.
>> Have you promised Jules?
>> I have since promised Jules.
>> Okay. So you want Jules
to go to the Final Four?
>> I do.
>> (snarling)
My hackles came up, and they're
still up.
You know, whatever happens, you
know, "Vengeance is mine,"
sayeth the jury.
>> That's cute.
She'll love it.
>> Eliza's mom will
probably be leaving soon,
and everybody's doing a little
something that maybe she can
pass on to our loved ones.
>> This is for Laurie.
>> Something for them to
remember us by and let them know
we're thinking about them.
>> This has been so great, Mom.
This has just been so great.
>> There's the boat.
>> But Mama....
I love you so much.
>> I love you so much, too.
>> Having my mom here has
definitely motivated me and made
me know that I can get through
this and I'm almost there, and
it's just so wonderful that she
got to spend this time with me.
>> Take this, too.
Keep warm.
>> Okay.
>> You're a good mom.
>> The shirt off my back.
>> She took the shirt off
her back and gave it to me
because I don't have anything
with sleeves even.
>> She came out and stripped
to her panties and left
in only her bra.
She is our kind of woman.
>> ALL: Bye!
>> There's one big one
right there.
>> Ami, Twila and I went
to get manioc.
And, you know, I wanted to hear
what Twila had to say about this
whole Chad and Chris scam.
>> I could tell you all
kinds of things people's
approached me with, Leann;
all kinds of things.
It doesn't matter.
My heart has stayed true to you
and Ami.
>> But you know what?
Any time that any guy comes to
me or talks to me, I tell y'all.
Any time that there's anything
said... just, just listen.
Don't get defensive.
Just understand how that kinda
doesn't really look so good.
>> They were trying to
work me like crazy.
>> Why don't you just
shut 'em down?
>> Why don't you say,
"Absolutely not.
There's no way in hell.
Go run on back to
your little buddies and..."?
>> Why do you have to
appease them?
>> Why do you even
listen to two words?
"I have nothing to hear.
Nothing... Bye... See ya."
I just think Twila got really
twisted up in her idea of what
making peace is and what the
right and wrong thing to do is
when it comes to a team.
>> I feel like a little
bit of a fool because I do have
some mistrust for you now.
But, um, I give you my word.
>> And I give you mine.
On my son, I swear, and you all
know how much I love that boy.
I swear to you.
>> Do you feel good about
that decision?
Because you don't seem like you
feel very good about that.
>> I-I feel guarded.
>> Don't.
Don't feel guarded.
I swore to Ami and Leann on my
son's name that I was with them
100%.
But maybe if I won a million
dollars, God would forgive me.
I don't know.
I hope.
>> Yeah.
>> Julie's pretty much
been my informant.
She informed me that their
flower power again; girls
strong.
Julie let me know that my head
is on the chopping block and I
have to win immunity to stay in
the game.
>> "To save your own skin,
you'll need more than just
will, brains and brawn,
determination and skill.
Yes, it's a race, so you must
hurry,
Only one will be safe and
one more joins the jury."
>> The race is on.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm going to win
immunity, guaranteed.
That's the prediction.
I'll make it right now.
Daugherty's going to win
immunity.
It's a fact.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Take back immunity, Twila.
Immunity back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you are
going to run it in pairs.
Let's bring in the people you're
going to pair up with.
Come on in.
>> Oh, my God.
(cheering)
>> PROBST: I think you know
these guys-- your loved ones.
They're still here.
They're gonna run it with you.
(cheering)
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: All right.
Your loved ones are down to a
one-in-seven shot at a million
bucks.
The only way to guarantee they
get to a one-in-six shot is to
have this around their neck.
That's where you're going to
either help them or potentially
hurt them.
Here's how it's going to work:
Each pair will be designated a
color.
The loved ones will be
blindfolded.
The survivors will verbally
direct their loved ones to
retrieve three bags of puzzle
pieces.
Once you have all three bags,
take off your blindfold, start
putting the puzzle together.
The first pair to finish their
puzzle wins immunity for their
survivor.
We will randomly draw for
position.
We'll get started.
This is going to be fun.
>> Ow!
>> PROBST: For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Laurie, spread your
feet and walk, walk, walk!
>> Left, Annie, left.
>> To your right, to your right!
>> Left, left.
>> To your right, to your
right, Laurie!
Straight, straight!
Go, Laurie.
>> Keep going right, go.
Keep going right! Right, right!
>> You're going to your right!
>> Turn around!
Teri, turn around!
>> Keep going, you got it.
You got it!
There you go, babe!
Yeah!
Yoo-whoo!
I love my girl!
>> Straight, straight,
straight, straight.
Right! Right there!
>> Stop!
Stop, Laurie.
No! No! Not there, there.
Untie it!
You're going to have to go
faster!
>> You got it, baby.
Drop it.
Good job.
Now keep walking.
>> PROBST: Crissy, back with the
first bag for Ami.
>> Keep going, keep going!
One more!
Yes!
That one, yes!
That's it.
>> Drop the bag! Drop the bag!
>> PROBST: James drops his first
bag.
He's back on the course.
>> No, no, no!
Turn around!
Listen to me!
>> PROBST: Susan getting closer
to her daughter, further away
from her bags.
>> Stop! Drop it!
Turn around.
>> PROBST: Laurie has her first
bag.
She's heading out for her
second.
>> To your right.
Go to your right.
Jimmy, to your other right.
>> Come on!
Straight, straight!
Drop it.
>> PROBST: Annie back with her
first bag for Scout.
She's back on the course.
>> I said straight!
Faster, faster!
Straight! No!
>> Good job.
You're coming straight to my
voice, baby.
I love you.
Drop the bag.
>> PROBST: Crissy back with a
second bag for Ami.
>> Go around the pole!
Come on, Laurie!
Walk faster!
Let's go, Laurie!
Come on, Laurie!
Keep coming!
Keep coming, Laurie!
Nothing in front of you!
Drop it!
Turn around!
>> PROBST: Laurie back with her
second bag.
>> Hurry, Teri!
>> What?
>> Good girl, yes.
Just hop over it.
>> There, there! Left!
Laurie, to your left!
Right there!
>> Turn to your right.
Turn... now drop the bag.
Drop it.
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfold, Crissy.
Ami and Crissy can start working
on the puzzle.
>> Stop, Annie!
Back up, back up!
No, no!
Yes!
>> Drop it!
Drop it!
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfold, Laurie.
Start putting the puzzle
together.
>> Come on, baby.
>> I think this goes down here.
>> Yeah, they got blue on top.
>> PROBST: It's going to be a
race between the puzzle-makers
now.
Chris and Laurie
versus Ami and Crissy.
>> To your right.
Drop it.
Take off your blindfold.
>> PROBST: Scout and Annie are
now in it.
>> Hurry!
Take off the...
>> Come on, come on!
Take it off, take it off!
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfold.
Justin and Julie are now in
this.
>> Can you hear me, Teri?
>> No.
>> Then why don't you
just sit down and stop?
>> Right to my voice,
right to my voice.
Come on, come on, son.
Right there.
Take your blindfold off.
>> PROBST: James is back with
his third bag.
Twila and James now working on
the puzzle.
>> We need something to
build on.
>> PROBST: Ami and Crissy having
trouble with the puzzle.
Chris working furiously to make
up time.
>> Faster!
Yeah, there you are.
>> Oh, good.
>> PROBST: Ami and Crissy
getting very close.
Chris and Laurie still fighting.
Immunity at stake.
Somebody going home tonight.
>> Right here, right here.
>> Huh?
>> PROBST: And they have it!
Ami wins immunity!
>> PROBST: All right, guys, fall
in right here in front of the
towers.
Ami, come on over.
Turn around.
Let's put this on.
Nicely done.
Good communication with your
partner.
As a result, you are safe.
Tonight's Tribal Council.
For the loved ones, one of your
survivors, this game is about to
end.
Tonight at Tribal Council,
somebody's going to be voted
out.
Say your good-byes.
>> PROBST: All right, loved
ones, head back the same way
you came.
You got to go.
>> Bye, everyone.
>> Bye, Annie.
>> PROBST: Sort of a strange
cacophony of emotion there.
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody else going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
I'll see you at Tribal Council.
>> So Ami won the
immunity challenge, and that
freed us up to vote for who we
were going to vote for next,
which was Chris.
For some reason, it didn't feel
right that Chris was going to
go home and Eliza wasn't.
>> I'll go with you.
>> I'm going to head
down toward that big one.
>> So we went for a
little walk in the woods.
And we decided as a group,
"Let's talk really, like, who
deserves to stay."
>> Something just doesn't sit
right with me, the fact
that for some reason,
it doesn't sit completely right
with me.
>> If you had to make a
make a decision right now...?
>> It don't matter to me.
I mean, you all know how I
feel.
>> I just feel like we've
come this far on principle.
>> Of having all women
together?
>> Yes, but yet, we did
vote Lisa off.
>> We've been talking
about Eliza getting off every
damn time.
>> Every time.
>> I think Chris should go
next, but it's not setting
really well for Leann, so if she
decides that it's not right,
then I'm going to stick with
what she says.
>> All right, we've made
our decision.
>> GROUP: All right.
>> We just really hope it
doesn't mess us up in the long
run and he wins immunity the
next couple of times.
That would be really bad.
>> So, I mean, it's 100%
but if it does change,
I'll tell you, but I don't
think, I swear...
>> How, how, how is that
going to swing, me not going
home?
>> Because, I mean,
everyone just thinks you deserve
it more.
Are you surprised?
>> I'm happy.
I mean, I'm pumped.
It's like being in a tornado.
It is crazy.
I don't even have to do
something to change the tide of
the game.
There's six women living with
me-- they'll change it
themselves.
It can be set in stone who's
going home, and five minutes
later, I'm not going home and I
ain't done a damn thing to
change it.
I'm just sitting there by the
fire.
So I make my way out to get some
wood and Twila says to me
while we're filling this crate,
"You know, you can change this
game completely."
So I'm thinking, "I'm all ears,
Twila."
>> Think about it.
>> You are so right.
>> If you would just get
Eliza, say, "If you want to
change this whole outlook, vote
this way, you've got three other
people backing you up."
>> Guaranteed?
Scout's a guarantee?
>> Guaranteed.
I swore on my son's name.
May God forgive me for saying
that, because it's not the right
thing to do, but it's time for
something to change.
Ami and Leann just act like
they're so much better than
everybody else and they've got
this all wrapped up in their
back pocket, and, and it just
freaking pisses me off.
>> 'Cause right now, I'm
still in...
>> I'm not going to.
You have my word.
I'm not going to, Twila.
>> I'll get this.
Am I willing to do it?
Damn right I'm willing to do it.
I'll turn the tide, I'll take
the risk right now.
So I talked to Eliza.
Here's the bottom line:
Julie told me, "You're staying,
you're not going home tonight.
We're voting for Eliza."
That's the exact words I was
told, okay?
Listen, Eliza.
You don't have to go home
tonight.
All's you got to do is one
thing.
>> Okay, what do I have
to do?
>> This is how you can stay.
>> Chris pulls me aside
and says, "Twila and Scout
discussed with him the
possibility of changing this
game around, and the only way
to do it would be with my vote.
>> You have my word,
I swear to you.
>> But I don't trust
Scout and Twila, that's what
scares me.
>> You do not have to
worry about Scout and Twila.
I swear, I have talked...
>> I think this is a big
plot and I'm gonna go home.
>> I don't know how to
reassure you.
I am just telling you the truth.
I've never lied to you.
I'm not using you.
>> But the thing that
worries me is that Scout and
Twila are lying to both of us.
>> Just please take this risk.
>> PROBST: Now bring in the
jury.
Sarge and Chad, voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
Okay.
The last three days have had a
lot of emotion.
Eliza, did having your mom here
wake you up to how close you
are to winning this thing?
>> Um, yes, having gotten
to the point of the family visit
in this game made me realize
how far along we really are,
because we have talked about
this on day seven maybe, and it
was, it was a long-term goal for
all of us.
>> PROBST: Chris, what was it
like to be in an immunity
challenge where, clearly, you,
of all people, have definitely
felt on your heels for a while.
Now you have your fiancée, who
can help you or hurt you in
this game, depending on how well
you do?
>> I knew that, uh, she
was wanting to give it 110%.
It meant a lot to her to come
through and, you know, get me
immunity.
Um, we worked hard together and
she gave it 110%.
I love her to death.
She did a great job today.
>> PROBST: Now, at the other end
of the spectrum, Leann, you
seemed just so happy to have
Teri there that you were taking
more of the moment of a
friendship thing, "Look what
we're doing together, and if I
don't win immunity, I don't win
immunity."
>> Well, I really wanted to win.
I mean, I set out to win, but,
you know, you get halfway
through and you realize there's
not a chance in hell you're
going to win it.
Then I just thought it was
funny.
Why not laugh with it?
I'm not going to have her feel
bad about it.
That would be horrible.
>> PROBST: Well, it seems to me
that Chris, out of everybody
here, was connecting with Laurie
in a way like nobody else was,
which is regardless of what's
happening, I got to win this
thing.
>> I didn't tell her it
was life or death for me.
I didn't feel like it was.
>> PROBST: Eliza, once again,
you brought your bag.
>> Jeff...
>> PROBST: You're becoming the
girl who cried wolf.
>> But you know what?
It's, like, "Oh, Eliza was
just being paranoid, Eliza's
just being paranoid."
And then every time I get back
to camp and I find out, "Oh, my
God, I was this close to being
voted off."
It is not paranoia.
It is valid 100%.
And I very well might be going
home tonight.
No joke.
>> PROBST: I don't think it is a
joke.
I just know you've said it at
every single Tribal Council.
>> And at every Tribal Council,
I have almost been voted off.
Honestly.
>> PROBST: Chris, as the
outsider, is there any tension
with this tribe, because what
you guys show me is very
happy-go-lucky and everybody's
having a good time.
>> Um, it's me and six
women-- six women.
There's tension between six
women.
I don't care what anybody says.
I can see and feel the tension,
and whether it be them playing
the game and strategizing or
figuring out, you know, who
they want to go home next,
there's always that feeling
that, you know, something's
going on that not all of them
are always agreeing.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Ami, you have immunity.
As always, you can keep it or
assign it to somebody else.
>> I'm going to keep it.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Ami; everybody else is fair
game.
It is time to vote.
Leann, you're up.
>> My vote's for Eliza.
Um, group consensus.
Everybody agreed, but you are
like a little sister.
>> Sorry, Eliza.
I had to stick with the team,
and I guess it's your time to
go.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Eliza.
Leann.
One vote Eliza, one vote Leann.
Eliza.
Two votes Eliza, one vote Leann.
Three votes Eliza, one vote
Leann.
Three votes Eliza, two votes
We're tied.
Three votes Leann, three votes
Eliza.
I'll read the last vote.
12th person voted out
of Survivor: Vanuatu:
Leann.
Bring me your torch.
Leann, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, as the last vote
was read, there were some very
smug looks; other faces were
absolutely shocked.
Nine days left, this game has
just been turned on its head.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> All I can say was that
was a really nice move.
>> Screwed you, didn't it?
>> You didn't screw me.
I'm still in the game.
>> We have been waiting
for an opportunity to turn
this game.
>> The bitterness started
as soon as we got back to camp.
It's going to be good.
>> PROBST: And the surprises
just keep coming.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I am just floored.
I just got done saying how it
wasn't a life-or-death situation
for me at today's challenge.
I was fooled.
I was fooled big-time.
I'd love to know who voted for
me 'cause I am just freakin'
flabbergasted at how someone
could just lie directly to your
face.
I feel like the world's biggest
idiot.