>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor:
>> Scout and Twila come to
me and Chad, wantin' to form
an alliance with us.
I swear to God, on my family's
lives.
>> As the last man standing,
Chris made an attempt
to save himself.
>> I narced out Scout and Twila.
It's gonna be a mess.
>> PROBST: And then there were
seven.
At the reward challenge,
the winner's going to get a one-
hour real-time e-mail back-and-
forth chat.
But first the Survivors were
allowed a brief hello to their
loved ones.
>> I miss you so much.
>> PROBST: All right, Twila,
you've got to say your
good-byes.
>> I've got to say good-bye,
buddy.
>> PROBST: "Grapefruit"
is right.
Eliza won reward.
Nice job.
And then got a big surprise.
Come on out, Susan.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: It's not a one-hour
chat.
It's an overnight chat.
>> PROBST: Back at camp...
>> There's our shelter.
>> PROBST: ...while Eliza
enjoyed her mom's company...
>> Oh, it looks great.
>> PROBST: ...Leann confronted
Scout about scheming with
the guys.
>> It was Chad's idea, and that
is the God's honest truth.
>> PROBST: The next morning,
Eliza's mom departed.
>> ALL: Bye.
>> It doesn't matter.
My heart has stayed true.
>> PROBST: And Twila made a bold
move to gain Ami and Leann's
trust.
>> On my son, I swear...
I swore on my son's name that I
was with them 100%, but maybe,
if I won a million dollars,
God would forgive me.
>> PROBST: Immunity-- back up
for grabs.
At the immunity challenge...
Come on in.
...the loved ones returned to
participate.
Survivors ready...
go!
Knowing he was on the chopping
block, Chris gave it his all.
But in a tight race, Ami and her
partner solved the puzzle first.
Ami wins immunity.
Back at camp, the tide
changed...
>> Chris deserves to stay.
>> PROBST: ...when the women's
alliance agreed to oust Eliza
before Chris.
>> Think about it.
>> PROBST: But Twila approached
Chris with a different plan...
>> PROBST: ...one that would
uproot Ami's powerful alliance
of women.
>> I'll turn the tide.
I'll take the risk right now.
>> PROBST: With Tribal Council
looming, Chris told Eliza the
women's alliance turned on her
and he offered her an
opportunity to save herself.
>> But I don't trust Scout
and Twila.
That's what scares me.
>> Just please take this risk.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Twila and Chris' plan worked.
Eliza joined them in voting out
Leann.
Leann, the tribe has spoken.
The all-women's alliance and
Ami's power position had
finally fallen apart.
Nine days left, this game has
just been turned on its head.
Six are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( theme song playing )
>> All I can say was that
was a really nice move.
>> I felt like we was going to
get all screwed over, so I
felt like I'd take up for the
little guy.
>> "Take up for the little guy."
That's cute.
Well, you're taking up for your
own guy, not for the little guy.
You're the one who made the
four-way alliance.
"Yeah, I'm down, totally
all the way.
Yeah, I'm in."
>> Screwed you, didn't it?
>> You didn't screw me.
I'm still in the game.
You screwed Leann.
I'm still here, baby, kicking
hard.
>> The bitterness started
as soon as we got back to camp.
I'm living with five wildcats
right now.
It's gonna be good.
>> You're always trying to keep
Eliza in it just for your
benefit to go forward.
>> It's all of a sudden
convenient for you to want to
keep Eliza in when before, every
single vote, you guys were like,
"Let's get rid of Eliza, let's
get rid of Eliza."
>> I know, but who saved
my ass tonight, when I was
really going to go home.
>> Honey, you've been really
about ready to go home...
>> Me, me.
>> ...nine million times.
I'm sorry, that's the truth of
my life, that I'm pretty happy.
>> You're putting Twila down.
>> Twila put herself down.
I didn't swear on my family
members.
I'm disappointed in Twila.
Promising on her son's life just
kind of disgusts me.
I lost all respect for Twila.
I don't know if I could ever
have respect for that woman
again.
>> The only thing, and
I'll be honest with you...
>> Ooh, I'm listening, big ears.
What?
>> Well, that's the thing
right there.
You and Leann and Julie thought
you all was so friggin' high and
mighty.
>> High and mighty?
>> You're dang right.
You're dang right.
We've overthrown the queen and
the little princess.
People like that just piss me
off because they think they are
so much better than every
freakin' body else.
We've got the power.
Chris, I, Scout, we have the
power now.
I have a great mind sometimes.
I love it.
>> Ami, you're cocky.
>> I'm cocky.
I'm also one of the most giving,
loving, caring people.
It's a nice balance.
I'm competing with all my heart
now.
I've got no cushions.
I've got no buddy to rely on.
It's me all the way.
>> Underwater.
Water's women.
I want this so bad.
I got mail, and it's gonna
be a good one.
"Today you'll push your limits
of swimming, balance and diving.
A test of will and stamina for
the last six still surviving.
A game-changing reward with
rejuvenating power, fuel for
your body, fuel for your soul
and a hot, relaxing shower."
>> Thank God.
>> I need fuel for my soul.
>> We're all hungry.
We all want food.
I'm just praying Eliza wins
because Eliza looks like a
little stick girl.
I've been calling her Olive Oyl.
>> I'm starving to death.
You better take me in if you win
the reward.
You better take me, Twila.
>> She needs to win.
>> No way.
>> Oh, my.
>> That's a nice car.
>> PROBST: Well, rather than
just tell you about your reward,
I thought I'd drive it over.
( whoops )
>> Nice.
>> PROBST: For the winner of
today's challenge an all-new
Pontiac G-6...
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: ...panoramic roof,
remote start, good-looking car.
That's just part of what you're
playing for.
The winner of this challenge,
plus the person who finishes
second and the person who
finishes third will leave in
this car.
You'll drive to a Vanuatu
ocean-side resort to get a hot
shower, go down to the beach
and have some cocktails and then
when you're ready, you'll have
dinner, and because I want you
to know exactly what you're
playing for, I have the actual
menu from the restaurant.
>> ALL: Oh...
>> Garlic bread.
>> PROBST: You can have as many
items as you want.
You can eat until the restaurant
closes...
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: And then you'll get a
good night's sleep on a
comfortable bed and come back in
the morning.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: All right.
Let's get to the challenge.
You're going to start on the
beach.
You'll swim out and race across
a series of outrigger canoes,
floating platforms and balance
beams.
When you get to the end of the
course, you'll dive in where you
will find three flags waiting
for you.
Retrieve one flag at a time,
bring it back to the beach.
First person to get all three
flags back wins the car.
First three to finish, the
overnight reward.
Let's hit it.
For reward... Survivors, ready?
Go!
Ami, Chris, Twila, Eliza, first
up on the obstacle course.
Twila goes in.
Scout giving it everything she
has.
Ami first in to dive for her
flag.
Eliza right behind, Chris going
for his flag.
Ami coming back with her first
flag and Julie going for a flag.
Scout... struggling.
Eliza coming back with a flag.
Chris back with a flag.
Chris pulls himself up onto the
platform.
Ami swimming back to shore with
her first flag.
Eliza, Chris, Julie, right on
her tail.
Twila has her first flag.
She's heading back.
Ami back with her first flag,
Eliza right behind, Chris on
her tail.
Julie still in it.
Twila having a heck of a time
getting back.
Eliza hangs her first flag.
Chris with his first flag.
Julie back with her first flag.
Ami still in the lead.
Scout in the water heading for
her first flag.
Chris using every part of the
course to stay out of the water.
Scout coming back with her first
flag.
Ami with her second flag.
Ami with only one flag left.
Eliza right behind.
Going to have to make up some
time.
Julie and Chris battling for
that third spot.
Ami still in the lead and the
woman who wouldn't quit, Scout,
making her way back.
Ami falls in.
Eliza closing the gap.
Ami back in, going for her third
and final flag.
Eliza right behind.
( gasping )
Julie with a big lead over Chris
for third.
Julie falls in.
Ami in the water and Eliza
gaining on Ami who is having
trouble getting back on the
course.
Chris and Ami playing chicken,
Eliza passes Ami.
It's between Eliza and Ami.
Ami back in the water.
Takes a hard fall.
It is Eliza's challenge to win
if she can finish.
With that, Eliza is going to win
the Pontiac G-6.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Nice job.
Ami finishes second.
She'll be going on the reward
with Eliza.
It's coming down to Chris
and Julie.
>> PROBST: Chris and Julie both
out of the water at the same
time.
Both worn out.
Both want to eat.
Julie falls in the water.
Chris stays on the course.
He has the lead.
Julie is going to have
to catch up.
Chris goes in the water.
Now Julie can make up time.
Julie and Chris dead even,
looking for that last spot on
the overnight reward.
It's down to Chris and Julie and
they are dead even going into
the water.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: They are neck and
neck.
>> Push, push, push.
( all shouting )
>> PROBST: Chris, the third
place finisher, going on the
overnight reward.
Great effort.
Eliza, Pontiac G-6 is yours.
>> I can't believe that.
>> PROBST: The overnight reward
is for all three of you.
The keys are waiting.
They're in the ignition.
Have a good trip.
>> Good job, Eliza.
>> PROBST: All right, guys.
Head on back to camp.
( cheers )
>> Oh, yeah!
>> This is sweet, isn't it?
>> Yeah.
Good job, Eliza.
>> I won the car.
I don't think that's sunk in
yet.
I still can't really believe
that.
It was gorgeous.
We had the windows open.
The sunroof was open.
It was just amazing.
>> Look at how beautiful
the beach is.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> This is paradise.
>> Yes, it is.
>> Hello, welcome.
>> Hi.
>> This is our bungalow.
>> There you are.
>> Oh, a bed and pillows.
>> Here are our robes.
It was just wonderful.
They told us to put our clothes
in this hamper and they would
wash them for us.
>> Toilet paper!
>> Sounds lovely.
And then we just decided to take
a shower immediately because we
had to take off all our clothes
anyhow.
>> I washed my hair two times
and scrubbed every part of
my body.
I actually feel human again.
I smell good.
Oh, it's heaven.
>> We all got to shower.
They didn't leave me no hot
water.
Bitches.
>> I don't... I can't
even describe it.
>> No, it's heaven.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I'm really sorry that I
voted for you.
>> I know.
>> I really should have trusted
in you a lot more than I
did and I'm really sorry.
>> It's okay.
>> I mean it from the
bottom of my heart.
>> I forgive you.
>> I'm sad that I got
pulled into Scout and Twila's,
like, nastiness towards you.
It makes me sad.
The fact that Scout keeps
talking down to me, I don't
appreciate very much.
>> I'm used to it.
She stopped talking down to me,
oh, about yesterday when she
needed my vote.
>> Hi, handsome.
>> I am clean.
>> Oh, doesn't it feel good?
>> I didn't want to get out.
>> The reward was beautiful.
We sat out by the ocean in
robes, like Hugh Heffner-- drink
in hand, hors d'oeuvres.
( moans ) Mm...
>> I have a feeling we're going
to be making that sound a
lot tonight.
Oh, my God.
We get entertainment.
>> It's a band.
Some Vanuatu people came out and
sang to us, and they were
dressed in vibrant orange with
big smiles on their faces, it
was beautiful.
>> ♪ Vanuatu
You look so green and lovely
Beautiful beds,
♪ Beautiful beach,
Lovely restaurants
and resort... ♪
>> The best reward ever.
It was totally out of a dream.
I mean, all of us, we just
couldn't wipe the smiles off our
faces.
( singing )
( cheering )
>> That was awesome.
>> I think every time we get
a water challenge, I drink
half the damn ocean. Man...
>> I wish we'd have just
a water challenge without
everything else added to it.
When I got back from that reward
challenge, I was angry.
>> The fact that I can't
physically show myself better in
the game, you know, it's
humiliating, because, given the
body that I had six years ago, I
could physically outdo anybody
that's out here right now.
Eliza kicked some butt on that.
>> Nice car.
>> I swear, I thought Ami
won that.
I can't believe that Eliza split
her butt.
I loved it.
>> She did. I'm so glad.
>> So what do you think
they are doing right now?
No, never mind, I don't want to
talk about it.
>> It ain't going to happen.
Liza, she's solid.
>> Ami is going to be smooth
talking Eliza tonight.
She will definitely be doing
some maneuvering.
Will it work?
I pray to God it don't.
>> I'm just so glad that
she and Chris are there
together.
That's going to make a
difference.
>> I want to try a bite of
yours, Chris, if you don't mind.
>> Yeah, it is awesome.
We had a really good meal, ate
as much as we could, just great
food.
I feel myself getting full.
I'm not stopping any time soon.
>> I'm not full before
dessert, that's for sure.
( laughing )
Food was unbelievable, and the
company was great, too.
I was really glad that Eliza,
Chris and I had won together.
♪ What an interesting game it's
been. ♪
Listen, I know you guys want to
get rid of me because I'm the
physical power player, I know
that.
But something that I think would
be really smart for you guys is
to break up Scout and Twila.
That's something you two should
talk about, but I think it'd
make a better position for the
two of you in the long run.
Please excuse me for one second.
>> She's so phony!
Does she think I'm stupid, you
know?
She's still working Eliza,
though.
She's strategizing, she's
playing the game.
>> It's not a bad idea to
break them up.
We would be in the final four
even if you, me and...
>> Not Ami.
We're pure final four, and if we
change anything nothing is
guaranteed.
Final four, and look at our
competition, a 60-year-old woman
and Twila.
I mean, why don't we just get
the checks out now.
I mean, you going to go cruising
in your new car as soon as you
get it?
>> Yeah.
>> I am definitely realistic
enough to keep tabs on
Eliza and comfort myself by
talking to her and hear her
reassure me that she knows
what's best for her.
I'm counting on the fact that
Eliza is mentally strong.
>> How you doing, Chris?
Is it comfortable?
>> Yeah, I can definitely
sleep out here.
>> Good night, Chris.
>> Good night.
( chuckles )
>> You know what, it is ironic
that Scout and Twila are the
ones who've been pushing to
get me voted off all along, yet
neither one of them has ever
picked up the pen and written my
name down. Ever.
>> It makes me want to puke
listening to you say how "Scout
and Twila have never written my
name down, they are so great."
>> I'm not saying they're
so great.
But, if it hadn't been for them,
then I wouldn't be here.
>> You know what, if it hadn't
been for me 50 million times
turning the tides and letting
you know what was going on.
>> I know.
>> Every single time I had
your back, every single vote I
proved it.
>> Ami has stood up for
me a lot of times.
Ami has been the one to say,
"No, I don't want to vote
Eliza off.
No, I'm not voting for Eliza."
Ami has been like a big sister
to me out here.
I'm pissed at myself, at my
decision...
>> Honey, you don't need to
be pissed at yourself.
>> I know, but more than
anything else I just got my
feelings hurt.
>> We should stop talking
about it, because I don't expect
any miracle from you.
I should just be quiet.
>> I woke up this morning
and I saw Ami, Eliza and Chris
walking back from the reward.
>> Hi, pretty.
>> Mm, you smell nice.
And it was great to have a new
smell in camp, definitely.
Especially for Chris, because
Chris stinks.
He doesn't stink anymore.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I know, right.
>> Oh, gosh...
Was it wonderful?
>> It was.
It was fun.
Hey, T.
>> I'm sure Ami worked on
Eliza pretty hard yesterday,
trying to get her to swing a
vote their way, you know, and
I am very worried about that.
Ami is so pissed off at me and
Scout, no telling what else she
will do.
>> Let me put your finger
right on it.
>> I got it.
>> I think it's too short
for you to get.
You got it.
>> I got it.
>> I'm going to go get wood.
>> Will you do mine?
>> It is annoying that they are
sitting there in the beauty shop
plucking hairs and we really
need to gather wood, but Ami
is a control freak.
She likes to control her world
and everyone in it.
>> She is the most jealous
person I've ever met.
I was thinking about it,
because, back in her day, she
probably was a lot more fit and
active and she thinks she could
have kicked my ass.
>> That's a big issue for her.
>> Yeah.
>> She's humiliated.
>> Scout, I think she's
irritated with me for some
reason, whether it's because
she's older and I'm younger and
I still have my body and she...
I don't know what it is.
But after Tribal Council the
other night, Scout has got me
pissed off.
Um, is that leftover manioc
stew?
I might cook some fish.
>> You know what?
We don't have much manioc left,
and we have...
>> I just brought back,
like, 20 pounds of manioc.
Are you kidding me?
I just went out hunting for food
all day long.
>> ...on that very back
garden...
>> You're kidding me right now.
You're telling me we don't have
enough food for me to make
another pot of manioc.
>> We have this much right
here...
>> That's the funniest
thing I've heard all day.
It's like Scout put a pile of
cayenne pepper in my pants and
said, "Hey, let's dance."
Well, I'm ready to dance.
I've lost all respect, all
anything for Twila.
But Scout hasn't been voted for
once, and I think it's important
she sees her name can be written
down, too, just like anybody
else.
The chance of Scout being in the
top two makes me sick,
like, just makes me sick.
>> They are a bunch of alley
cats going at it, and
strategically, this is the
best thing for me.
I don't even think they're
looking at me.
I mean, I'm just sitting back
and watching 'em shoot
each other.
>> Get your own damn blanket.
That's ours.
>> But Ami needs to go home.
She's definitely a threat.
I mean, we knocked her off of
her horse, thank God.
But who's to say she ain't to
get up, dust herself off, climb
back on and pull something off?
>> Tree mail.
>> Looks like a spirit button.
>> Ooh.
"Some are faster and stronger
and smarter and such, but this
time you are safe if you have
the right touch."
Ooh.
>> What do you think it is?
>> It's gonna be balancing,
something balancing
something on something.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ( chuckles ): Another
interesting challenge.
It's hard to tell.
I have not been capable of
overcoming the physical
challenges against these women,
so I want immunity.
I'm still the only guy here.
I'm the only man standing.
Immunity is all that's gonna
make me safe.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Ami, give it up.
>> I don't think it'll come off.
It's stuck.
>> PROBST: Try.
>> ( Ami laughs )
>> PROBST: Once again immunity
back up for grabs.
For today's Immunity Challenge,
you're going to take part in a
Survivor version of
shuffleboard.
Represented on our board are the
islands of Vanuatu.
You will each have five pucks.
Your goal: land as many of your
pucks as you can on any part of
the different islands.
You can also use them
defensively to knock another
tribe member off of an island.
The only way to guarantee that
once you're on an island you
stay there is drop it in the
volcano.
There that can't be knocked out.
At the end of the game, the
tribe member who has the most
pucks touching any part of any
of the islands wins immunity.
We'll draw numbers to determine
your order, and we will get
going.
Okay, we have randomly drawn to
determine your order.
Chris, you'll go first this
round.
Chris with his first shot.
Mm.
Twila, get us on the board.
Eliza.
Trying to land on an island.
That'll count.
>> Nice job, Eliza.
>> PROBST: Ami.
The big island.
And look at that.
That'll count.
Julie.
Your first shot of the first
round.
Julie banks and in the volcano!
( cheering )
Right in the volcano.
Nobody can knock you out.
That point's gonna be safe the
whole game.
Scout looking to get on the
board.
Aw, no love.
At the end of the first round,
Eliza with one, Julie with one,
and Ami with one. Twila.
Oh, look at that!
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: And that's a safe
point.
Nobody gonna knock that out.
Eliza.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Ami.
>> PROBST: Oh, so close.
Julie looking to go in the lead.
And she does.
>> Nice.
Julie with her second point.
Scout.
Chris.
Last shot of this round.
Up and over.
At the end of the second round,
Julie with two, Ami, Eliza,
Twila with one.
Eliza.
Ami.
Julie in the lead with two.
Nope.
Scout yet to get on the board.
That's close.
No.
>> Almost.
>> PROBST: Chris.
Chris is on.
Twila.
At the end of three rounds,
Julie with two, Chris, Ami,
Eliza, Twila with one.
And she's on.
Ami has her second point.
Julie with two, looking to add.
>> Close.
>> PROBST: Scout.
That'll do it!
>> There you go!
>> PROBST: Scout is on with her
first point.
Chris.
Chris knocks Julie off and puts
himself on the board.
>> Yeah, there you go!
>> PROBST: Chris and Ami now
tied at two.
Julie back to one.
Twila now has two.
>> Do it! Two!
>> PROBST: Eliza needs another
point to stay in it.
>> Oh, I just knocked
myself off!
>> PROBST: Instead of gaining a
point, Eliza just lost her
only point.
At end of four rounds, Ami,
Chris and Twila with two,
Julie and Scout with one.
Last round.
Julie needs another point to
stay in this.
And instead she just puts Twila
further on.
Scout.
She's going offensively.
Trying to score.
And she does!
Scout, Twila, Chris and Ami now
each with two.
Chris takes the lead with three.
Twila with her last shot.
She's just short.
Eliza, you're up.
No points, but you can play the
role of the spoiler, and you can
knock Chris off an island.
>> I missed entirely.
>> PROBST: Not even close.
One shot left. It is Ami.
If she scores or knocks Chris
off, we go to a tiebreaker.
She gonna go offense...
or defense?
Ami takes herself out.
Chris wins immunity!
>> Yes!
>> Yeah!
>> Good job, dude.
Yes. Way to go.
Way to go.
>> PROBST: All right, Chris,
come over here.
Turn around here, I'll put
this on you.
You're safe tonight at Tribal
Council.
With only six people left,
somebody is going home tonight.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: You have the
afternoon.
Should be an interesting one.
Head on back to camp.
>> Good job, Chris.
>> Thank you.
Finally.
>> Finally!
>> I won something.
Today was my day.
I was extremely happy to win
immunity.
It is a little bit humorous that
it did take a nonphysical
challenge to beat the chicks.
But I'm looking at it as though
I've achieved something great
here, and I have immunity.
That's all that matters
right now.
>> Can you believe I
knocked myself off?
>> I know.
>> Today was definitely one
of my weaker challenges, and it
just happens to be the challenge
that I needed the most.
So tonight's the night.
>> You do know she's got to go,
no matter what.
>> But, then, you're not gonna
turn around and vote for me,
are you?
>> No, hon. I gave you...
Well, I can't give you my word,
'cause you don't trust my word
no more.
>> I know, but it's hard 'cause,
you know, you swore on your son
and...
>> Yeah, I did do that, and
that was a mistake, and I
take it back.
>> But it still m...
>> Don't second-guess me.
I swear to you, you don't have
nothing to worry about.
Us four are solid.
I think Ami could influence
Eliza.
She's got the power.
She's got the wit and the
power to do it.
Ami has controlled this game
from the second day, and she's
very persuasive.
If she hadn't have been, them
other girls wouldn't have
followed her all this time.
Ami's got one day to work her
magic on Eliza.
I just worry, 'cause part of her
don't want to trust me yet,
you know.
>> Mm-hmm.
But I want you to know that I
feel like I've stood up for you
five million times, and if then
you kind of, like, throw me off
to the side at the very end of
the game, that would hurt my
feelings.
It's like, whatever.
Okay, so you don't give a ...
then that's how the game rolls.
I really thought that I could go
through this game and play,
like, a fair game all the way
through and not have to play
dirty, and it just didn't
work out.
So I'm really vulnerable right
now, and Eliza would be the
only hope.
>> Is there any way they
can convince her that if she
comes with them, she'll have a
better chance or anything?
Is there any way?
>> No, because then they risk
a tie.
Eliza's not gonna risk no tie
vote.
That puts her in jeopardy.
If there is a tie, it's my
understanding that everyone
would have the opportunity to
vote again.
And if voting again did not
break the tie, the two people
being voted for, I think they
would get immunity, and the rest
of us would pull rocks, and
whoever drew a colored rock
goes home.
So Eliza could mess things
up real bad.
>> Yeah. Me, too.
>> It's really going to be tough
to vote for Ami, really hard,
because I like Ami a lot and I
like Julie a lot, too.
I have fun with them.
I connect with them.
They have been my friends since
really early on in this game.
Oh, my God, he's been off with
them all day.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God.
I just like spending
time with them.
They're just more fun
than you are.
>> Does she not want you to?
Who are you more sick of, Scout
or Twila?
>> Scout.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> How is that fair?
If it was a 3-3 vote, we just
went at Tribal, didn't mention
it at all...
>> Oh, my God, dude.
>> All of a sudden, bam,
and it would be... oh, she would
be so mad.
>> Dude, that that would
be the best.
It would be the best thing that
could happen in this game.
>> Feels good, doesn't it?
>> Right now Scout,
Twila and Chris think I'm, you
know, 100% solid in this final
four alliance, but I do have
reservations because I don't
think Scout or Twila will take
me to the final three.
Ami and Julie, on the other
hand, would take me, so I'm not
afraid to change things if I
think that it's going to get me
farther in this game.
>> Oh, there you are.
Eliza could go either way, but I
have a connection with Eliza so
I know that there is something
in her heart saying, "You
know what?
I really would like to have Ami
in the game," so anything could
happen.
>> PROBST: Now bring in the
jury, Sarge, Chad and Leann
voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
Well, the reactions while the
votes were being read at the
last Tribal went from one end to
the other, from smug to absolute
shock.
Ami, you were shocked.
>> Yeah, I was shocked.
Yeah, I thought I was going to
go home and sleep with Leann and
she wasn't coming home.
And once I saw her name once, I
knew something was definitely
wrong in my world.
>> PROBST: Scout, what is Chris
still doing here, because you're
the one who told me "I want the
women to stay strong and keep
together the whole game."
Clearly, the women have not
stayed strong.
>> Well, my desire was to
find out what would happen if
the women would stay strong and
would stay together, but once we
merged, several of us weren't
able to play the game.
We were sitting ducks.
And a position came along where
a group of us could make a
change in the game, so we did.
>> PROBST: It seems to me, you
wanted the women to stick
together only so long as it
served you and, the minute it
didn't, you would change
strategy.
There's nothing wrong with that,
but, clearly, this whole women
power thing is over.
Ami, based on the last vote, you
don't seem as much a part of
this right now.
>> I'm not any part of this
anymore, and I think when
somebody flat out just
disgustingly lies to you and
says things to you that I really
can't imagine, that person to me
is just written out of my life.
I don't have any part of that.
>> May I clear that up,
Jeff, thank you very much?
I did swear on my son's name and
I do ask forgiveness, but I am
not the only friggin' person
that has lied in this game!
Get over it!
Grow up, get on with it.
You've been had.
Screw you!
>> PROBST: Ami, you're laughing.
>> You can lie all you want
and that is part of this game,
but when you bring in the one
thing that you say is the most
sacred thing to you in the
world, the only thing that
matters, the only thing that
makes your heart really beat,
and then you lie on it, to me,
that is not worth a million
dollars.
That is not worth a gazillion
I was left sad, really sad
about that.
>> PROBST: So, Eliza, is this a
little bit of sour grapes for
Ami with her attitude?
>> I don't think it's sour
grapes, because when you
feel close to someone and then
they do what you feel like is
backstabbing you, it hurts.
Twila swore on her son, the one
thing that someone would say to
convince me, oh, they must be
true to their word and having a
response to that, I think, is
absolutely natural.
>> PROBST: How are you feeling
about your vote last Tribal
Council, when Leann was clearly
hurt?
>> It was awful.
It was really hard.
I think that's one of the
hardest aspects of this game.
I never imagined how close of
friendships I would form here
and that it would really hurt to
vote people off.
>> PROBST: Would you miss Ami if
she was gone?
>> Yep, a lot.
>> PROBST: What would you miss
about her?
>> Ami is the person who every
time we get tree mail she
turns to me and says, "Okay,
Eliza, what's the challenge
going to be?" and I try figure
it out.
And she's like, "Oh, my God,
you're going to be awesome at
that challenge and you're just
going to do great," and, you
know, she's just-- the big
sister I never had, and, yeah,
I'd miss Ami a lot.
>> Stop crying.
>> PROBST: Ami, would you miss
Eliza?
>> AMI: I would miss Eliza
a lot.
I've really, really grown to
love Eliza.
By far, she has changed more
than anyone in this game.
She's been willing to change.
She should be proud of herself.
>> PROBST: And it is time to
vote.
Chris, you have immunity.
I can't imagine that you would
want to give it up.
>> No, I'm not giving up
immunity.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote
for Chris.
Everybody else is fair game.
Twila, you're up.
>> Drama queen to the end.
>> Well, Scout, you're pretty
good at hiding your nasty side,
but when your true colors come
out, they are no part of any
rainbow I've ever seen.
>> Ami, queens get dethroned,
and a lightning will strike a
lone tree on top of a mountain
faster than anything.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote Ami.
Scout.
One vote Scout.
Ami.
Two votes Ami, one vote Scout.
Scout.
We're tied, two votes Ami, two
votes Scout.
Ami.
That's three votes Ami, two
votes Scout.
I'll read the last vote.
13th person voted out of
Survivor: Vanuatu, Ami.
You can bring me your torch.
>> Good luck, all you young'uns.
>> PROBST: Ami, the tribe
has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, tonight's Tribal Council
illuminated the undeniable
tension and the frayed nerves
that exist within this tribe
after 33 days.
With only six days left,
it's only going to get worse.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> I am so sorry that I
ever made that statement.
>> PROBST: Twila unleashes her
dark side.
>> You can kiss my ass.
>> Twila flipped out and
I'm going to completely use it
against her later on.
>> I think you're a liar, T.
I think you're a liar.
>> PROBST: Eliza and Twila
have it out.
>> I'm having some fun
right now.
It's dangerous though.
>> First off, I just have to
laugh.
If I could just hold Twila
underwater for two minutes, I
think it would make me feel
better, but I really feel my
integrity is still complete, and
I can't say that for all those
people on the tribe still.
I've gained some really
important friends in my life--
Leann, Jules, Eliza.
I love those girls.