>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Tom brought in the big one.
( laughing )
>> How did you get it?
>> I hit it with the machete.
>> Oh, now, who's
the great white shark killer?
>> And wham!
>> It's gonna be a lot harder
to vote him off now.
>> Yeah!
( Tom whoops )
>> PROBST: When tree mail
arrived, the tribes learned
they were to build an SOS signal
that could be seen from the air.
>> Little rain...
>> I say we burn
our friggin' shelter.
>> PROBST: Ulong jumped right
in, while Koror took a more
methodical approach.
>> The first thing that we want
to do is find the right
location.
>> PROBST: When the plane flew
over Ulong, the drop master
was not impressed.
>> Unless you're flying
right over the top,
it would be hard to see.
>> PROBST: And although Koror
had trouble with their fire...
Do you have enough information
to make a decision?
>> Yes, I do.
>> PROBST: ...it was their
signal that best caught the eye
of the drop master.
( cheering )
>> I'm so happy!
>> In the box was three
bottles of red wine...
>> Cheese tortellini
and tomato sauce.
>> And then we had all of these
military food packages
that you could heat up
and eat as meals.
>> To a great tribe.
>> PROBST: At Ulong, the tribe
took the loss hard.
>> We lost the reward challenge
because they worked harder.
Or I'm sure they worked
smarter, knowing them.
>> PROBST: At Koror, Jenn and
Gregg's budding romance
raised some red flags.
>> I'm concerned
with Gregg and Jenn.
It just could be a monkey wrench
that we don't see coming.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Ulong couldn't get it
together.
Ulong may be worse off
than when you started.
>> Back.
>> PROBST: And Coby moved his
tribe to another Koror victory.
>> Left-- empty spot,
and I swear we got it.
>> PROBST: And with that,
Koror wins immunity
for the sixth straight time.
Before Tribal Council,
Stephenie feared the worst
when Bobby Jon couldn't commit.
>> I thought we were sticking
together, no matter what.
>> Well, it's just kind
of a toss up, you know?
>> You're not sticking
with your word, then?
>> I don't really want
to talk about it.
>> I can tell by the way he's
acting he's gonna vote for me.
>> PROBST: But the votes came
in, and Ibrehem was voted out,
when Bobby Jon honored his
arrangement with Stephenie
to be the last
two members of Ulong.
Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( blowing )
>> There it goes.
>> I thank you
for keeping your word.
>> Yeah?
>> I was a little nervous.
I-I knew it was
a hard decision for you.
>> It's over. It's done.
There wasn't no good way
to do it, you know?
>> I know.
Tonight we went to Tribal
Council, and I was
really nervous.
I really thought
I was gonna be the one to go.
Bobby Jon, he beat
around the bush.
He didn't really want
to give me an answer on
whether he was going to vote
for me or Ibrehem,
but luckily he kept his word
and Ibrehem went home.
>> Ibrehem and I, we had a
friendship, we had a bond, but
in competition you have
to rule out feelings, and
I just thought
Stephenie has performed
better than Ibrehem
at challenges, so... I did what
was best for the tribe.
>> I'm glad that we're still
here.
I'm still ready
to bring home a victory.
I think we can do it.
>> Yeah, I do, too.
>> It was tough with three,
and it's already weird being
here only with two, but
I don't feel
that my time is up here.
I'm still ready to win,
and it's clear now
that Bobby Jon and I
are the two people
best for the job right now.
( buzzing )
>> Eww! Go!
Get out of here!
>> What's with the rats today?
There's like six of them playing
in front of the steps.
>> They're looking for...
>> Yeah.
>> Just took them a few days
to lose their fear.
The rats, they're
going crazy today.
I don't know if, uh, if we've
gotten sloppy with food
or we're cutting the coconuts
too close to the camp or...
I just think it's that the rats
have got comfortable with us
and realize that we're not
a threat to them.
>> The rats have become
bolder and bolder, and it's all
our tribe's fault because nobody
will listen to me.
There's coconut everywhere,
so of course the rats are going
to become more and more bold.
They're eating our coconut,
which is all over the camp
because people won't clean up.
So every bit of rat that we get
all over us is deserved.
>> You are?
>> Uh, I'm not smelling
it anymore.
I've told people for days.
I have told Tom every day
since he caught that shark
to move his damn shark head,
because it stinks,
there's flies everywhere.
It's not even 20 feet
from our camp.
So I got up this morning,
I moved the shark head,
I moved the guts because nobody
was doing anything, as usual.
I'm the one who has to get the
firewood, I'm the one who has to
keep the fire going, I'm the one
whoa has to boil the water.
I'm the one who has
to go hunt food.
Those girls don't do anything,
especially Jennifer,
Katie and Janu.
Katie and Jennifer don't do
anything all day long.
I've never seen them touch a
piece of wood since we've been
here, and now Janu is on her
eighth straight day of,
"Boo-hoo! I want to go home."
Would you quit already?
Get out of the game.
You know, I'm too much of a
feminist to watch this happen.
These Alpha males are just
totally waiting on them hand
and foot, and the girls
are loving it.
They're eating it up.
It's making me sick.
I want to take
all three of those girls
and push them in that fire.
( sighs ): Oh...
>> Come on in, Koror.
We'll now bring in Ulong.
Ibrehem voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
>> Hi.
>> PROBST: You're only two,
but you're still a tribe.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get
to today's challenge.
It is going to require
an adventurous spirit,
a willingness to try
something new
and an overall open
attitude toward life.
It is a food challenge.
The food you're going
to be eating is a delicacy.
It's also very nutritious.
It's from this part of the
world, and it's called balute.
Balute is a fertilized egg
that contains
partially-formed duckling.
These ducks
are about 20 days old.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: You can see the
beak... and it is full of
protein.
Here's how it'll work.
We're gonna go in rounds.
Each round, we will
increase the number
of balute you eat.
In the first round
you'll eat one balute,
then two balute,
then three balute
and finally four balute.
There will be four rounds.
Each time you get it down, you
score a point for your tribe.
At the end of four rounds,
whoever has the most
points wins reward.
Makes sense?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: I know you both have
showers.
What you don't have for
those showers is fresh water.
First part of your reward,
55 gallons of fresh water
in a tank with a showerhead
delivered to your camp.
That's water
you don't have to find,
water you don't have
to bring back,
water you don't have to boil.
To go along with that,
because, trust me,
you guys reek...
( laughing )
...a little
luxury gift bag here.
>> Wow.
( cheering )
Everything you need to get
clean, get that taste
out of your mouth,
get that smell off your body.
Do not underestimate
how revitalizing that can be
to get clean again.
That's what you're playing for.
Koror, because you have
six extra members now,
you're sitting six people out.
Just tell me the two
that are going to compete.
Ian... and Tom.
It'll be Ian and Tom
versus Steph and Bobby Jon.
Everybody else,
take a spot on the bench.
Round one, come on up.
This is not a race.
This is just get it down.
Here's how you know
when you're finished.
Show me an empty mouth.
I'll say you're good.
Once I say you're good, if it
comes back up, it's fine.
Balute is served.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
>> Ready.
>> PROBST: Eat.
>> How's it, Tom?
>> PROBST: Bites right in.
>> Come on, Tom, it's beer.
>> PROBST: So does Steph.
>> Down.
>> PROBST: Tom's clean.
He's good.
>> Give me a wink, Tom.
Come on, show me something.
All right.
>> PROBST: That's good.
Koror and Ulong both score.
We're tied one-one
after the first round.
>> Watch the beak.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Next two, come on up.
>> "Watch the beak."
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Eat.
>> Mmm!
That was a juicy one.
>> Echh.
( Ian chuckles )
>> Oh... Umm...
What's going through
your head, Ian?
>> There was some egg shell
in that one.
>> PROBST: Sure that was what
was the crunchy part?
>> I don't know.
>> I don't either.
>> But I need the soap.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, we got a
little piece right there on the
plate.
Let me see that thing.
That'll work.
All right. That'll work.
>> All right, Ian.
>> Good job, Ian.
>> PROBST: We're good after two
rounds.
Tom and Steph,
we are tied at two-two.
You now have three balute
to get down.
Survivors ready... and eat.
>> PROBST: Thinking at all about
what you're eating, Steph?
>> Eggs.
>> PROBST: Eggs.
It's just eggs.
>> Just don't look at it.
>> I got a chirp out of that
one.
>> Mmm. Mmm.
>> PROBST: Tom has three down.
He's clearing that mouth.
That's good.
>> Damn, Tom.
>> Hungry.
>> I can feel the feet
a little, too-- they scratch.
>> PROBST: That looks good.
Tom and Steph--
they've downed three balute.
We are tied three-three,
moving into the last round.
Ian, Bobby Jon,
four balute waiting for you.
Survivors ready...
eat.
>> Come on, Ian.
>> Good job, I.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon not messing
around.
He's almost done.
>> Come on, I.
>> Come on, I. Just keep...
>> It's all right, I.
Get it down.
>> PROBST: Open that mouth,
brother.
That's good.
Ian gets down all four
just like that.
Head back.
We are tied four-four.
>> PROBST: Okay, moving into
a tiebreaker.
You'll pick
your strongest person.
You'll eat five balute.
It's a time trial.
First one to get five down
wins reward.
>> I was hoping
for a few more of these.
>> PROBST: Who's it going to be
for Koror?
>> It's going to be Tom.
>> PROBST: Tom's going to take
the five.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: And Bobby Jon.
Come on up.
>> Come on, Tom.
>> Attaboy, Tom. Come on.
>> PROBST: At stake:
55 gallons of fresh water.
That is a lot of water.
Plus everything you need
to get clean-- get this taste
out of your mouth.
First one to get all five down,
show me an empty mouth,
wins reward.
Survivors ready...
eat.
Bobby Jon two-fisting it.
>> Good job. Good job.
>> PROBST: Tom trying,
taking nibbles from both.
>> Come on, now.
>> PROBST: Gonna come down
to an empty mouth.
>> Guiness, Guiness.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon shoving
that fifth one in there.
>> Get it down, Tom!
>> PROBST: Keep it in there.
Keep it over the plate.
>> You can do it, Tom.
Mind over matter, fireman.
>> You got it, Tom.
>> Nice job. Nice job.
Nice job, Tom.
>> Come on, Tom.
You got it, Tom.
Come on, now.
>> PROBST: Tom's got his fifth
one in his mouth,
but he's got to get it down.
>> Nice work, Tom.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon trying
to shove it down.
>> Come on, Tom. Koror!
You got it, Tom.
( clapping )
>> Think about how dirty I am
now, come on.
>> You can do it, Tom.
Show him that mouth.
>> Come on, Tom.
>> Just swallow, Tom.
Hurry, before him.
>> Bobby Jon's getting it.
>> Hurry!
>> Swallow. Swallow.
Swallow it, Bobby Jon.
>> He's almost there. Come on.
>> PROBST: Tom very close.
( Bobby Jon retching )
Tom's got it for Koror!
( groans )
( cheering )
Might as well finish it.
Right, Bobby Jon?
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Tom?
Rinse that out of your mouth.
A little Scope will make
that taste go away, huh?
>> Hook a brother
up, will you?
>> This tastes good enough
to drink.
>> PROBST: This challenge is
over for Ulong.
Grab your stuff,
head on back to camp, guys.
>> Man, I almost had him.
>> PROBST: Koror, 55 gallons of
fresh water in a tank, with a
showerhead, will be delivered to
your camp.
You can take this back with you.
Congratulations.
>> That's the soap.
I'm getting the dirt off!
( cheering )
>> All right!
>> Whoo!
>> The challenge today
was for a reward.
We got 55 gallons of water,
which is great,
and we won a basket of shampoo
and conditioner and toothpaste
and toothbrushes.
>> Cheers.
>> I'd say I'm a big fan
of the Scope mouthwash.
I particularly like
the Citrus Splash.
Tastes a little bit like
oranges.
( chuckling )
>> We all took a swig,
and just... it felt so good
'cause it was just tingling.
It was wonderful.
>> Did y'all want to come see
what you won back here?
New water thing.
>> Seeing the big drum up
there...
Oh! We have a shower.
I was looking forward
to feeling human for one day.
You think you should
use all that for showers?
Given that we're all still
drinking poisoned water.
>> We should use none of it
for showers.
>> I agree.
>>> I think we should
take off that showerhead
and fill canteens right out of
that spigot.
>> I think most people want
a shower, though.
Don't you?
>> Let's see how much
is over there.
>> Can we just have
one shower, and then...
>> We can, but we're still in
a survival situation here.
Jenn was crestfallen that she
wasn't going to get in.
I had to assert myself,
and it's something
I've been trying not to do.
But there were people
within the tribe who
actually thought that the first
fresh water that we've seen
in 19 days should actually
be used for shower purposes.
It's ridiculous.
>> What do you think, Jenn?
>> Jenn wants a shower.
>> Everybody takes a shower,
we're down to two-thirds.
I agree.
>> Tom is the one who spoke up.
"Well, I think we need
to, uh, conserve, you know,
and use that water
for drinking."
And it's 55 gallons of water!
I mean, come on.
You can't let us use,
like, a gallon or two?
>> I vote for not using the
fresh water, but like, I know
there's some people who
really want a shower
and really want
that comfort, so...
>> No, it's all right.
>> Nobody wants to speak up,
and I'm not going
to be that person.
I could see that coming back
to haunt me.
"Oh, Jenn really wanted to use,
you know,
the clean water for her bath."
>> So we're okay?
Everybody's good
with the decision?
>> Everyone's good, or...?
>> Yeah. Yeah, makes sense.
>> He really is not letting it
be a vote.
Maybe, in the end, that'll
make him be voted off, you know,
for being such a sourpuss
about the whole thing.
>> You see how much of that
stuff I had left in my hand?
Okay?
>> Yeah, I know.
It's always like that.
It's, like, we're there, but we
miss it by, like, an inch.
>> Today's defeat
is heartbreaking.
I mean, I had my throat open
as much as I could,
shoving it in there, but Tom,
he shoved his in faster.
Well, I'm getting tired
of losing to him, you know?
>> Right.
For some reason, you keep
matching up against him.
Well, you're the strongest
on our tribe, and he's
the strongest on theirs.
That's why.
>> I feel like I can beat
anybody else on that tribe.
>> I know.
>> If you want to
know the truth.
>> I know you can.
That's why you're not
going up against anybody else.
You're going up against him.
>> It just seems like Tom
beats me every single time, and
that's something
that's getting real, real old,
so I'm real pissed right now.
I mean, I see fire.
>> Bobby Jon?
I think he's been
too positive about the losses.
He's, like, "It's okay.
We lost again.
We'll get them next time."
But he's starting
to get frustrated.
I don't know.
I guess guys
need to throw things,
punch things, make noise--
whatever they can to feel manly
when they're pissed off.
But, half the time,
he scares me.
Bobby Jon is sick of losing,
and I think he's finally,
finally starting
to take it to heart.
So, I was actually happy
to see him mad like that.
>> Being undefeated is glorious,
but it's a lot of days
of monotony.
We've been with the same people
for many days now, but
things are going to change real
quick around here.
No more Happy Koror Day.
No more... ( cheering )
It's going to be...
( growls )...
eating each other.
>> If they turn, then they need
to be broken up.
Gregg and Jenn-- they're part
of the alliance.
But I'm still worried about
them switching over and trying
to pick Tom and I off.
They're two votes strong.
That makes it a threat.
I think they're definitely
using their relationship
for strategic advantage, so we
know, going into it, you know,
that we're going to need to take
one of them out eventually.
We're all family, but there's
a business side to it, too,
so we are on the verge
of utter ridiculousness,
for sure, and I can't wait.
>> Well, listen, we
got good news.
Stephenie's still there...
>> We really need...
we're gonna need...
>> We needed that.
We have to keep that quiet here.
You can't slip in front
of Gregg, you know, and Jenn,
'cause just... 'cause we
are all together.
You got to keep that quiet.
Katie and Ian and I hooked up
on day two, and said let's see
how far we can take this.
And Stephenie also
was part of that group.
Except for myself,
Ian and Katie,
nobody even knows that there is
a relationship that Stephenie
would be the wolf
in the sheep's clothing
that they wouldn't
even see coming.
>> Final four is me,
you, Stephenie and-and Katie.
>> Right.
( grunts )
>> You all right?
>> Yeah. I just make noises.
I feel like if I scream
at it that, uh...
>> My boyfriend does that,
and I want to friggin' kill him.
>> Really?
>> It's hard being here
with just Bobby Jon.
Sometimes I don't know what
to say to him, you know?
It's just the two of us left.
We don't have a lot in common.
It's just tough.
( Bobby Jon burps )
Bobby Jon is totally turning
into a caveman.
( blowing gourd )
I mean, I'm not going to lie.
Like, I am disgusting,
but I scrub so much
with that sand--
my armpits, and my whole body--
that I really don't think
I smell that bad.
But Bobby Jon?
He's just gross.
He is always dirty.
Always.
( crunching )
And then he eats everything
and anything.
Like, today, we caught a crab.
And he's eating the whole
thing, and I'm, like, you know,
you're supposed to eat the
white meat inside.
Not the shell.
Oh, man...
>> I know that's gross.
>> Snot rocket.
>> I'm sorry. I got to do it.
>> Occasionally, I will turn
around and see him
blowing a snot rocket
straight out directly in
the middle of where we sleep.
He does apologize, but, um...
it's nasty.
It's hard, 'cause I-I think
about Koror all the time,
and I know that they are just,
like, living the life
over there.
They're having
the time of their life,
and here me and Bobby Jon are,
you know, busting our butts
to try to keep the fire
in the cave going.
I thought this was going
to be a piece of cake.
I could do this.
It's totally me.
I'm totally cut out for this.
And I am.
And I still believe that.
But it's tough.
Damn!
>> Got to let it down.
>> Holy crap!
Oh, man, need help?
( grunts )
>> Just getting that outrigger
into the water
damn near killed us.
Good job.
>> One, two, three.
( grunting )
( loud grunting )
>> Rest.
>> If I make it through this,
I can make it through anything.
( grunting )
I mean, it's tough physically,
it's tough mentally,
it's tough emotionally.
It's hard, it's like
we're halfway through,
but we have so long to go.
( voice breaking ): And...
I'm trying to be so strong
and it's like,
you can only do so much work.
And it's hard, it's like,
you're out here with no one.
And it is really hard.
I won't give up hope,
but I feel like we're at,
like, a dead end.
>> We are really
kind of down right now
'cause we're really tired
and we're really hungry,
but we're just going to keep
trying and trying.
You know, we don't give up,
and I-I value that.
>> I got one. I got one!
>> Wow!
Good job!
>> A school of needlefish swam
up, and I just shot
right in the middle of them
and happened to get one.
So I kind of felt like,
you know,
like I'd accomplished something.
Golly, the meat!
( whistles )
>> That's going to be
a lot to eat tonight.
Oh, my God.
>> How good is it?
>> Oh, my God.
This is so good.
There's so much meat.
The fish that we had, it was
like the best thing I ever had
in my life.
You can feel the protein going
into your body.
>> This is the breakfast
of champions.
>> We are having a feast.
It's been 21 days
and we've barely had any fish,
so it was a really nice treat
to have that.
And that's all we needed
to really get our spirits up.
>> Puzzle.
>> "Sink or swim."
>> "Sink or swim.
Think and swim."
>> "Today they mean the same.
For the tribe who can't do
either, one more will
leave the game."
>> It's imperative we win today,
because it's for immunity,
and if we lose,
there will be no more Ulong.
It's pretty much do or die.
>> It really is.
>> We're pretty tough
competitors, so I think today
immunity is going to be
Ulong's, finally,
'cause I'm pretty good
at this stuff.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> We are.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Janu has it today.
Immunity once again
back up for grabs.
Ulong, that means
anyone can win.
Okay, for today's challenge,
you're going to swim out
to a series of pontoons.
Underneath the pontoons
there's a rope
that leads to four bags
of puzzle pieces
spaced out along the course.
First person will swim out,
pull yourself along the rope
to the first bag of puzzle
pieces and unclip the bag.
You'll then hop up on the
pontoon, cross the balance beam
come back to the start.
Then the next person will go
out to collect the second bag.
You will alternate
until you have all four bags.
Once you have all four bags
of puzzle pieces, open them up,
start putting together
a word scramble puzzle.
Once you have the puzzle
put together,
start circling the words
that are on your puzzle board.
Any time two words intersect,
take that intersecting letter
and write it on a letter cube.
When you've found all the words,
take the intersecting letters,
use them
to form a three-word phrase.
That phrase holds the key
to immunity.
Koror, you're only running
two members.
The only people who cannot
participate are the people
who participated yesterday,
that's Ian and Tom.
Who are the two today?
>> Me and Coby.
>> PROBST: Coby and Gregg.
All right, everybody else
take a spot on the bench.
Wait for my "go."
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready... go!
Gregg and Steph
into the water first.
Pull yourself underwater looking
for a bag of puzzle pieces.
Steph gets to the pontoon first.
Gregg right behind.
>> Come on, Steph.
>> PROBST: Gregg and Steph both
up with their puzzle pieces.
Puzzle pieces are not light.
Working the balance beam.
Gregg with a bit of a lead.
Steph right behind.
>> All right, Gregg.
Looking good.
>> PROBST: Gregg's back.
Coby heading out.
Steph back,
Bobby Jon heading out.
Bobby Jon trying
to make up some ground
almost walked on water.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Coby trying to find
the puzzle pieces.
Bobby Jon making up some ground.
Coby's got them, he's up.
( applause )
Bobby Jon's got his, he's up.
We're dead even.
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon is taking
the lead for Ulong.
>> You got it, Bobby Jon!
>> Bring it in, Cobe!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon heading
back with the second bag
of puzzle pieces.
Steph heading back out
for Ulong.
Gregg heading back out
for Koror.
Steph has the third bag
for Ulong.
>> There you go, Steph,
take your time, baby, come on!
>> PROBST: Gregg has the third
bag for Koror.
Steph-- no trouble
with the balance beams,
making short order of it.
>> All right, Gregg!
>> PROBST: Ulong with their
third bag-- one more to go.
Bobby Jon heads out
looking for that last bag.
He's got a big lead.
Coby heads out, lot of ground
to make up for Koror.
Coby's making up some ground,
closing that gap.
>> Whoo!
( panting )
>> Bobby Jon!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon struggling
to get that last bag.
Bobby Jon has it for Ulong.
Coby has it for Koror.
We're dead even.
>> Good job, Coby.
>> Yeah, Coby.
>> Push, push, push!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon is back.
Start opening.
Coby is back, now moving on
to the puzzle phase
of this challenge.
It is anybody's game.
Koror going right to work
on the puzzle board.
>> Come on, bring it up there.
>> PROBST: Koror making
progress.
Koror has their puzzle together.
They are going to start solving
the word scramble.
>> It's not there.
>> This has got to be it.
The one we had before.
Are we missing a piece?
>> PROBST: Ulong struggling
to get the puzzle together.
Koror is already finding words.
Ulong has solved their puzzle.
>> Go, start going.
>> PROBST: Koror has all of
their words, they are now
looking for a three-word phrase.
Steph not embarrassed
to just look next door.
>> Hell, no, not now.
>> PROBST: Coby going to cover
it up now.
Ulong not quitting.
>> Right here.
>> This is wrong.
>> Jeff.
>> PROBST: Koror thinks
they have it.
"Victory at sea."
Koror is right.
Koror wins immunity again.
( cheering )
>> Awesome!
Koror, once again immunity
is going back to camp.
Gregg.
>> Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Ulong, I wish I had
better news.
Tribal Council tonight,
because there are only two
of you, there will be no vote.
There will be an individual
immunity challenge.
Loser goes home.
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff.
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> Nice job!
>> Yay!
>> Clean sweep.
>> Way to rock it out, guys.
>> A lot of effort.
>> We won another immunity,
which means that we've won
every single immunity.
It's mind-boggling.
I never fathomed coming into
this game I would be on a team
this strong.
>> I loved that we started out,
it was like,
the three oldest people,
the gay guy...
>> The skinny, gangly guy...
>> The tall, skinny guy,
the dancer...
>> The skinny showgirl.
>> You know?
>> We were absolutely
the underdogs.
We were silly and goofy
and kind of quirky-looking,
and I cannot believe we won
immunity every single time.
>> We all made the jury.
Isn't that crazy?
>> It's a good thing.
>> Today meant a lot
because my whole life I've
wanted to be part of a team.
Because, you know,
when I was a kid,
the jocks would make fun of me,
I'd quit, I'd run off crying.
That was one of the reasons
I came here.
>> Good job, Coby.
>> You know what?
Every time we've
done a physical challenge,
you've stepped up, man.
Like, you've been very physical.
>> Don't make me cry.
I never got to be part of a
team,much less a winning team.
As a kid I never played sports.
I was always called the girly
guy, you know, I was the sissy.
People would pick on me,
and I would just give up.
I ended up quitting school
because people made fun of me.
( voice breaking ): I've given
up a lot in my life.
But I wasn't going to let
anybody make me quit this time,
no matter how hard it is.
So nobody was gonna, nobody was
gonna take this away from me,
and that's why
I've worked so hard.
'Cause I'm not quitting.
>> Well, we didn't get immunity.
The final challenge.
Today we lost our last shot
at immunity.
We had a great lead.
We just suck at puzzles.
And it's, like, what can we do?
It's over now.
>> You know,
we've tried to prepare,
we've tried to strategize, we've
tried this, tried...
nothing has worked for this
tribe-- I mean, nothing.
In a way I feel like, you know,
I lost the thing today, you
know?
I felt like I was focused.
I felt like Stephenie
was focused.
I thought we were gonna win.
I don't know.
I've done all the grunting and
getting and going and climbing
and swinging from vines
and all that that I can do,
and now it's gonna be
between she and I.
I don't want to go home--
I'm gonna feel like a failure
if I go home right now.
You know how bad I'll feel?
>> That's what I said,
that's what I said.
>> Like, you know, like...
>> To not win one immunity?
I know.
Tonight we will go to Tribal
Council, and there will be
an individual immunity up for
grabs, some sort of challenge,
and we're gonna compete
against one another
to see who stays in the game.
>> There we go.
There we go.
Damn.
You always get it started.
You think, like, tonight whoever
stays will come back here
by themself?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> It's kind of scary,
because I don't know
what's gonna happen.
Like, Ulong will then be down
to one remaining member, and I
guess that person will come back
here by themselves?
It's gonna be tough, just one
person trying to do fire,
water, go fishing.
>> Yeah.
>> It was scary
just coming back here
with Bobby Jon, but at least I
knew I had him, because he does
a lot of the work around camp
that I can't do.
So if I'm here by myself,
that will be really scary.
>> It's gonna be weird.
>> I know.
( laughs )
>> There may never be a merge,
and it may just keep on going
one at a time, and if it does,
then I'm prepared for it.
I'm good at getting fire,
I know where every coconut tree
is, I know where every little
fishing hole is,
so I can stay out here
for weeks by myself.
>> It's tough because we were
teammates all along, and now
we're competing
against one another.
So it's do or die.
If I don't win tonight,
I'm out of the game completely.
If I win tonight, there is
a whole variety of things
that could happen.
Hey, we need to talk
'cause I, like, have no idea
what the hell
this immunity thing could be.
It's definitely a challenge,
but what kind, do you think?
>> Stephenie thinks nonstop.
I think she even thinks
when she sleeps.
So she's thinking right now.
"How am I gonna kick
Bobby Jon's ass?"
That's just how she is,
and when it comes down
to being, you know,
bad-ass to bad-ass,
I'll-I'll get... I'll get
just as bad-ass with anybody.
>> Let's go.
>> Let's do it.
>> All right.
>> I been doing
this little team thing,
and that's fine and cute,
and I enjoy it and it's great.
But I'm kind of getting tired
of the team thing.
It's done, you know?
This is team Bobby Jon
right now.
>> PROBST: So, what's it like
being a tribe of two?
This is new.
Steph, what was it like today?
>> Um, just enjoyed our time
together and just talked, and,
you know, we both think that
the strongest members
of Ulong remaining,
and whoever wins tonight
deserves to be here.
>> PROBST: Was today a little
bit bittersweet?
It's almost like
you're the final two,
but we're barely halfway
into this game.
>> You know, it's, like,
oh, we're the last two,
but, you know,
we've only knocked, like, one
little notch out of the game.
There's, like,
so many things left to do.
You got to go all the way,
and, you know, half's nothing.
>> PROBST: Has there been
a highlight for you
in these first 21 days,
Bobby Jon?
>> I think today was,
to be honest with you.
Catching, like, fish and, like,
having success,
you really learn that,
you know, hey, you know,
you can get by, and you can live
off, you know, Mother Nature.
>> PROBST: Steph, how do you
feel about your ability to
survive?
Have you learned a few things?
>> I have.
I learned a lot from
Bobby Jon, actually.
Still not so good
at spearing fish, but...
uh, I know how to...
>> She can get coconuts,
>> ...coconuts...
>> ...she can get crabs,
and she can start a fire.
>> I don't know how good myself,
but...
>> She can do anything a man
can do,I'll tell you that.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon,
what would you say after 21 days
is the key to survival?
What have you learned
that's most important?
>> Fire. Fire.
Definitely fire.
>> PROBST: Ability to make it?
Keep it going?
>> Both.
>> Ability it make it
and keep it going.
You know, we came in today
and it was out,
and we had to restart it.
You know, we just kind of looked
at each other like,
oh, no, here we go again.
This could take
an hour or longer.
>> PROBST: So, Steph,
would you agree with Bobby Jon--
is fire most essential?
I'm, like, frantic without fire.
Absolutely.
>> PROBST: All right,
let's get to your
immunity challenge.
You want to know what it is?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: It shouldn't surprise
you.
It is the key to survival:
the ability to make fire.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: You're both gonna
have 25 matches.
You will have a box of kindling
and coconut husk.
The first person to build a fire
with a flame high enough
to light their torch wins
immunity, stays in the game.
Loser... goes home.
Both feel confident
in your fire-making skills?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm not that good.
>> PROBST: All right, take a
spot over there, and we'll get
started.
>> Oh, man.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Survivors ready.
Begin.
Bobby Jon going right
for the coconut husk.
They each have the same box
of kindling and coconut husk.
And the same amount of matches.
And Steph going
for the coconut husk.
Bobby Jon has fire first.
Steph right behind.
Steph blowing on it.
That's using your brains.
Steph has a big flame.
Bobby Jon trying to keep up.
Steph's torch is lit!
Just like that,
this challenge is over.
Steph wins immunity.
Bobby Jon, I'm sorry,
for you it's over.
Steph, go ahead and have a seat
back on the bench.
Bobby Jon, you need
to get your torch.
>> Hey, good luck.
>> You, too.
>> Thank you. See ya.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, the tribe
definitely did not
speak tonight.
Nonetheless, it's time for
you to go.
So long.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Oh, my God.
This is crazy.
>> PROBST: It's just you.
>> It's just me now.
>> PROBST: What do you think
tonight's gonna be like?
>> It's gonna be scary.
I mean, I left camp
with the fire pretty stoked
and, uh, my bed already made,
in case I was coming back to it,
and lots of firewood.
So I'm kind of scared.
Hopefully, I'll have a good
night, and tomorrow,
God knows what that brings.
>> PROBST: We'll see what
tomorrow brings.
Grab your torch,
head on back to camp.
You're still alive.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> The three of us'll go?
>> PROBST: Tom offends Coby.
>> I'll be left out
again, as usual.
>> Coby... Coby...
>> Hello? I'm still here.
I'm still trying to participate,
you jerks.
>> PROBST: And Stephenie
struggles alone at Ulong.
>> This is scary as hell.
This is the scariest thing,
and the hardest thing
that I'll ever do.
>> I feel like a brand-new man,
I really do.
I wish I could keep going--
I have a lot left in me-- but
hopefully, I can turn that
energy and that attitude to
something positive from here on
out.
I'm definitely proud of
Stephenie, 'cause I think
she's honestly probably
the top player in the game.
I would just tell Stephenie
just keep on doing
what she's doing-- I mean,
the girl's almost invincible.