>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> Oh, my God, there were three!
>> PROBST: With their flint
to make fire at the bottom of
the ocean...
>> Oh, no!
>> PROBST: ...Koror had a
horrible night at their new
beach.
>> It was a mistake for us
to choose this island.
I regret that we didn't
think it through.
>> PROBST: At Ulong, Angie was
still feeling like an outsider.
>> I'm just making myself
a valuable asset to this tribe.
If I don't, I'll probably be on
the chopping block again.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
At the reward challenge,
the competition was brutal.
And Angie redeemed herself.
>> Good job, Angie!
>> PROBST: Angie is across.
Ulong wins reward!
Ulong walked away
with their first victory
as well as fishing gear...
Here's fire-- who wants it?
...and their own flint
to make fire.
At Koror...
>> I got it!
>> PROBST: Ian saved the day
when he helped salvage
the lost flint.
( cheering )
>> Getting the box was like
running a marathon
and winning first place.
>> Make love.
Don't blow too hard.
>> Who wants theirs first?
>> PROBST: Back at Ulong...
>> No, thank you.
I'm not hungry.
>> PROBST: Ashlee refused to
eat.
>> If we have someone
slowing us down, I hope that
that doesn't bring down
our team.
I think I'm going to crash.
>> PROBST: And the tribe noticed
sparks between Jeff and Kim.
>> Kim's been snuggling
on Jeff a lot.
I mean, two-people alliance
is a very strong alliance.
>> PROBST: At the next
challenge...
Kim, the only one yet to give it
a go for Ulong.
...Kim held Ulong back.
>> We gotta keep going.
We gotta keep going.
>> PROBST: Checking. Checking.
>> You sure?
>> PROBST: Koror!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Koror won their
second immunity in a row.
Back at Ulong,
Stephenie wanted Kim out.
>> We need to break
Kim and Jeff up.
I mean, she didn't even try
at the challenge.
She sat out there.
>> Yeah.
>> She didn't go underwater.
>> PROBST: But there was a
divide in the opinions.
>> I was thinking Ashlee.
She's breaking down, man.
I can tell she's breaking down.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Kim and Jeff's relationship
came out in the open.
Kim, when did you feel
the first initial seeds
of any attraction?
>> It's hot in here
all of a sudden.
>> All jokes aside, there's no
alliances being built here.
>> PROBST: But when the votes
came in...
Second person voted out
of Survivor: Palau...
...Ashlee was sent packing.
Ashlee, the tribe has spoken.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I really can't go back
there again.
Not soon.
We cannot lose any more reward.
We can't.
>> And, oh, Jeff was pretty
tough today, I thought.
>> That's the way this game
goes, you know?
>> Yeah.
I think Tribal Council tonight
told a lot 'cause Kim and Jeff
both got votes.
If we would have went
with our original votes,
Ashlee'd still be here,
and Kim'd be gone.
I think Kim's aware,
and I think Jeff's aware, too.
>> Are you serious?
>> Mm-hmm.
I know, Jeff totally pinpointed
you guys, like, were a couple
or something.
>> I know. It was obnoxious.
>> And you know what?
You can't be like, "No, we're
just like really good friends."
You have to be like, "Oh, yeah,
we're kind of attracted
to one another."
You know, like...
>> It pisses me off.
It really does piss me off.
>> At Tribal,
Jeff was pretty brutal.
He asked me about Kim and I.
I just basically said that
we're keeping each other warm.
We...
It really does help
to have someone next to you.
>> I think the thing
between me and Jeff
has just been exaggerated
by everybody talking about it.
I don't want people conjuring
this image up in their head
that's not accurate,
and thinking that
there's two personal lives,
it's like strategy or what.
I don't want that image.
>> Jeff Probst asked Kim and
Jeff if there's anything going
on, you know?
And they said, "No,
we're just buddies, cuddling."
Mm-mm-- everybody sees
what they're doing.
Right now they're cuddling.
Next week, they're going to be
making out.
You know, sucking face
and stuff.
She's a woman,
and all she has to her advantage
is her sexuality.
Kim's got to go.
I'm keeping an eye on them.
I got ears like a bat,
I'm telling you.
( distant thunder rolling )
( seagulls crying )
>> Oh, man, look at that out
there.
>> It's the shower
we were all looking for.
It's been raining
a couple times a day.
We have kind of a lame shelter,
and we're kind of limited
to supplies here.
We're getting wet at night,
and we need a better shelter.
>> I've been digging and
digging-- a heavy day it's been.
I was not gonna let it go.
I'm trying to focus on
that damn shelter.
It's been three days,
and it's still not finished.
This is just going to take
a little thinking, girls.
( grunting )
Nine strong has its
advantages and disadvantages,
'cause, obviously,
we're all still together,
we're still strong.
Yeah, I think people are
grating their nerves even worse
'cause, you know, you can't
ever get rid of anybody.
You know you're stuck with them.
>> I need to ask you something.
If you can find more bamboo,
do you think you can?
>> It's hard to find.
>> Even getting something
on the other side if possible
to block out the...
Someone needs to get up
in that tree and do the top.
Don't you think?
>> Yeah.
>> Won't be me.
>> Katie is a very...
I don't know what the word is;
it's not outspoken,
it's tart, you know?
Just that she has something
to say all the time
about everything.
>> What are you going to do
with those?
>> I'm just filling gaps here.
>> I'm thinking we could use
those for the bed.
>> There's more, a lot more.
And it's especially true
with me.
For seven days, I've been not
saying anything,
and I've just had it.
And I just decided to confront
her; I want it to stop.
And I've just had enough!
Now, I don't want to make waves.
>> And you're making waves.
>> No, this is between you and
me.
I'm not making a scene
in front of the tribe.
And I don't want to bring
anyone else into this.
>> Why are you all freaked out?
>> Because everything I say,
you have some snotty remark.
I throw a freakin' stick
in the fire, you're like,
"Oh, they say don't throw
sticks in the fire."
Don't tell me what to do, Katie!
Don't tell me what to do
anymore.
I'm done hearing it.
>> I was just sitting
on the edge of the boat.
She just comes up to me
and she's, like,
"Do you have a problem with me?"
And I'm like, "What?"
And I started laughing
'cause she was so irate.
>> You said the guys said,
"Don't throw sticks in the
fire," like, everything I say,
you're on me.
Get off me!
>> She wouldn't even give me
the time to respond
to any of her accusations.
She wanted to come up to me
and just tell me off.
And then she went off
and she left.
She turns and frowns.
Like, I couldn't stop laughing.
She's crazy.
She's completely lost it.
I don't need you yelling at me.
I think there's a better
way of doing this.
>> Okay.
>> If there wasn't any
animosity, there is now,
'cause I don't like
people yelling at me.
>> The repercussions of my
confronting Katie will be that
she will not talk to me,
and that's just fine with me.
Unfortunately,
there might be some tension
around the tribe as well.
You will always run the risk
if you're too confrontational
of being the one who's voted
off, but I haven't heard
my name come up.
It could change now
as a result of what I did.
>> PROBST: I'll now bring in
the new Ulong tribe.
Ashlee voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, you guys ready
for today's challenge?
>> We're ready.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge
is for a reward.
It is once again physical.
Here's how it works.
On my go,
a life ring will be released
from the bottom of the ocean.
Your goal?
Swim out, retrieve the ring,
bring it back to your
tribe-colored pontoon.
First tribe member to get
a hand on the pontoon
while having a hand
on the life ring
scores a point for their tribe.
Here's the catch.
Aside from punching
or otherwise intentionally
trying to hurt someone,
you can pretty much do whatever
you want to get that ring
and keep it and get back.
Push, pull, dunk, splash,
keeping in mind that ultimately
this is a social game.
And to win it,
you will need the votes
of the people you are living
with and competing against.
How you play it,
ultimately up to you.
First round, one man
from each tribe will square off.
Second round, one woman
After that,
we'll switch things up.
First tribe to score three
wins reward.
Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Full-on sewing kit.
>> Nice.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: I'm looking around,
I see a lot of people
in underwear.
We've got three buffs
working as skirts.
So, hopefully,
the reward will change
the way you guys look.
But if you are resourceful,
there are a lot of items
you can use around camp.
Worth playing for?
>> Hell, yeah.
>> PROBST: Koror, because you
have two extra members,
you're sitting two people out.
Who are you going to sit out?
>> Caryn and Willard.
>> PROBST: Caryn and Willard
will sit this one out.
Everybody else take a spot,
wait for my go.
All right, guys, first round
will be man versus man.
Who's running?
Tom and Jeff in the first round.
Survivors ready!
Go!
Strategy and physical are
going to play a part in this.
Jeff is going to hang back.
Jeff is going to let Tom
do the work.
>> Yeah!
>> Come on, Tom.
>> PROBST: The showdown is on.
Tom just put it around his
waist.
>> Good idea, Tom.
>> Drag him.
Drag him, Jeff.
Drag him.
>> Drag him, Jeff!
>> PROBST: Jeff dragging Tom,
using Tom's strategy against
him.
>> Drag him, Jeff!
>> Drag him!
>> PROBST: He's lost the life
ring!
Jeff has it.
Tom has it back.
>> Get it, Tom!
>> PROBST: It is a tug-of-war.
Jeff still pulling Tom.
>> Go, Jeff!
>> PROBST: Getting closer to his
pontoon.
>> Yes! Yes!
>> Go, Jeff! Go, Jeff!
>> Come on, Jeff!
>> PROBST: Jeff very close.
Jeff has it!
Ulong scores the first round.
>> It's all right, Tom.
>> PROBST: Next round is going
to be woman versus woman.
It's going to be Jenn and Steph.
Steph and Jenn.
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Steph with a big head
start.
>> Come on, let's go!
>> PROBST: Steph, strong
swimmer.
>> Come on, Steph!
>> PROBST: She's got the life
ring.
( cheering )
>> Go! Go right!
>> Come on, Steph!
>> PROBST: A little splashing
going on.
>> Don't let her do it.
Get her!
>> PROBST: Good old-fashioned
cat fight.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Jenn trying to dunk
Steph, but Steph takes Jenn
instead.
Steph seems to be pulling Jenn.
>> Keep swimming! You got it!
>> You got it, Steph.
You got it.
>> PROBST: It is a tug-of-war.
Steph getting closer
to her pontoon.
( cheering and whooping )
>> We got it.
>> Ulong scores the second
round!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Round three is one
guy and one girl from each
tribe-- Bobby Jon and Angie
taking on Gregg and Janu.
Ulong wins this,
they win reward.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Gregg hanging back defensively.
>> Come on, Angie!
>> Relax, buddy, relax.
>> Ready to...
>> Angie, dunk her!
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Angie dunking Janu,
taking her out of it.
Janu didn't like it.
>> Wow!
( cheering )
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Angie dunks Gregg!
>> Yeah!
>> Get her!
>> Come on, Angie!
>> PROBST: Gregg dunking
Bobby Jon.
This is as physical
as it's gotten.
Angie grabbing on to Gregg,
trying to hold him under.
>> Bobby, get over there!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon pulling
Gregg.
>> Get up here! Come on!
>> You got it!
>> PROBST: Gregg fighting back,
but it's not enough.
Angie gives him another dunk.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon very close.
( yells )
>> PROBST: Ulong wins reward!
( cheering )
( yells )
>> That's my boy.
>> Awesome job.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> PROBST: Koror, not much
to say.
It's a tough physical challenge.
Ulong earned it; they won it.
I got nothing for you.
Ulong, nice job.
Good strategy.
You guys worked well together.
Here's your reward.
Be inventive.
Head back to camp.
>> That was so awesome.
We totally kicked their ass.
>> You're so awesome.
You're so quick.
>> It was a total shutout.
I'm going to tell you what.
Mmm...
That's what I'm talking about.
We kicked tail today
and we won a lot of things.
We can make a lot of different
types of garments.
We have so many tools.
>> Look.
>> This is elastic.
>> You could use these...
>> This is what we need.
...as fishing hooks.
>> The reward we won
was a big, huge sewing kit.
I'm not a sewer.
I'm not a seamstress.
I have no idea
what I could do with it.
Buttons, and a jar.
We can do something
with this jar.
>> This here, you...
That's is going to be
our fishing line, right?
>> Yep, that little red, gold
stick.
>> I know I'm going to use
some of the line that we have
and some of the metal posts
that we have for fish hooks.
Slip off, whoever wants
to slip off,
whatnot, whatever, and, uh,
we'll get some of the minnows.
>> That sounds good.
>> Yeah, go get some minnows.
>> So we need to get
some wood up, too, before it
starts getting wet, 'cause it's
going to for sure rain.
It rains every afternoon here.
The win today definitely gave
us a huge momentum boost.
We still got a few things
to do, though.
There's a lot of stuff right now
that's not done
that we need to do,
so I'm just kind of like, if I
gotta do it, then I'll do it.
>> It's not much,
but I think they'll like it.
>> What are we going to do,
just sit here?
>> Looks like everybody died.
>> I'm very disappointed
in my tribe right now.
I mean, there's little things
that have to be done.
I'm not going to wait for
everybody to have a group
meeting.
Let's decide.
Well, we need to decide
and that's time,
and time's wasting.
>> Oh, so close.
>> You know, the first few days,
it was fine.
I like doing stuff for people.
But, man, they're going to let
you do everything out here
if you keep on doing it.
( stick thudding on coconuts )
>> Goodness.
( thudding )
There you go.
>> Especially Kim, I don't think
she understands
the value of work.
There's lots and lots of work
to do.
She doesn't really see that.
>> Are you tired?
>> No.
>> Are you crazy?
>> Yeah.
>> Bobby Jon really works his
booty off, almost to the point
where we are constantly
telling him to sit down,
you need to chill out.
I think he's playing his cards
in the beginning to be safe
and cement his place into the
group, and he'll be of no use
if, you know, he keeps doing
this for two weeks and, like,
crashes and burns.
>> We all took a walk down the
beach and spotted a couple
of banded sea snakes.
It's definitely a sea krait,
so just be careful.
They are very venomous, one of
the most venomous snakes
there is.
We're hungry,
and it was a big motivation.
The plan was to just
pin it down, hold it down
and then lop off its head.
Okay, I can take one chop
and be done.
>> They are poisonous snakes.
They're very poisonous snakes,
and they can cause cardiac
arrest, coma...
they can cause death, um,
with just one bite.
Ready?
>> Go.
>> Chop the snake!
Chop the snake!
>> We got him.
>> Keep going.
>> Sorry, buddy.
I'm sorry, buddy.
>> Ian chopped
the snake's head off.
He was so cute.
Like the whole time, he's all,
"Sorry, buddy, sorry, man.
Just got to do it, man, sorry."
( yells )
>> Okay, here's dinner.
>> You know, I work with
dolphins.
I love animals,
so to just kill a snake outright
and in cold blood wasn't for me.
So, I did feel bad.
>> Oh, no!
>> Koror!
Even without a head,
I'm still not convinced
he isn't going to bite me.
>> I was going to head back
with Katie and Jenn
to start the fire.
Tom and Ian, they found
three more snakes, and
they're, like, "Let's get these
while we can."
>> Nice little hari-kari stroke.
>> Are you ready? One...
>> Make it hard.
One, two, three.
>> He against the wall?
You got him?
>> Yeah, I got him pinned.
>> So he'll come out to fight.
When his head comes out,
man, lop it off.
There it is. There it is.
Get that head.
>> You got him?
>> We got him.
>> Got him?
>> That's it, Gregg.
>> Look, he's got something in
him, too, right, he just ate.
>> That's what we saw.
>> So it was maybe
a little foolhardy,
a little sense of adventure,
but, um...
obviously I've hooked up
with two other knuckleheads
who, uh, take fun in the
excitement of things like this.
And we're through.
>> Yes!
>> Ah!
We kind of let the carcasses
of the snakes hang out,
but as soon as we hung them
from the tree over the water,
we also noticed
that a young shark
came swimming and kept making
closer passes to it.
>> Oh, there it is.
That thing right there.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know it might be the blood
from the snakes dripping
in the water.
We kind of got interested
that maybe we could trade
our snake with a shark.
>> A few of 'em...
>> If I saw a shark at Jones
Beach on Long Island,
we would all be running
out of the water.
We see a shark fin go by here,
everybody runs into the water
with sticks in their hands.
>> Probably the stupidest thing
I've done in a while, but...
>> You know,
the motivation is there;
we have to get food in us.
>> See 'em?
>> They see it.
Yup, they're coming closer.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Oh, my friggin' gosh.
>> You think they're interested
in that?
>> Let's see if we can, uh...
They got, they got...
They keep getting...
Oh, here comes on.
Okay, here comes one.
Don't move. Don't move.
There he is. There he is.
Holy... Oh, he saw me.
>> Gosh, he came so close.
>> Hey, Jenn, you want
to chop up some more,
some more snake?
They really were close.
They were wily.
Close enough to make you
nervous, like, they come
straight at you and make you a
little bit heebie-jeebie.
Yeah, that's good stuff.
Nice and bloody.
Oh, that's nice and bloody.
>> It's a game of survival
as well as strategy,
and the survival aspect of it
is more real
than I ever imagined,
and also, the thought of having
shark steaks on a frying pan
is the motivation that takes
you past the fear of a shark.
>> There he is.
Oh, my gosh, he's right there.
Uh, two.
Two left.
Oh, man.
There's three of them around.
Bam! Bam! He took it.
Got really close.
>> They would get to just out
of reach of us.
I took a lunge at one
and missed,
but they knew we were there,
and would just probe so far,
but no closer.
We had sharpened sticks,
which I don't think would
really go through shark skin.
He's big enough to put a
hurting on you, that guy.
>> Yeah.
We're going to back off the...
the snakes and redouble our
effort on the sharks,
I think is our plan right now.
We're going to get a shark.
>> Ow.
Going out to use the little
boys' room real quick,
and came walking down the beach,
stepped on a loose coconut.
Just my luck, rolled it on my
ankle that I had problems with
last year.
I'm just going to try
and keep it up right now.
Hopefully,
get all the fluids out of it.
Maybe wake up in the morning
and be a new man.
Let's hope.
>> What's up, buddy?
>> How you doing?
>> Pretty good. How are you?
>> I'm all right.
Making yourself a diaper?
Be careful, buddy.
You might be piercing something
you don't want to pierce.
You need help, but I'm not going
to help you.
>> Right, right, right, right.
No, it's all good.
>> There's a lot on my mind
this morning.
Got a lack of sleep last night
because of my ankle.
I tried to keep it elevated
throughout the night,
but the pain is still there,
so I'm going to try
and take it easy today
and, you know, I want to try
and save my energy
until maybe our next challenge
so that I can do my best.
>> We got a challenge.
>> We got a challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> How's your ankle feel?
>> Horrible.
>> Horrible?
>> "The weight of the weak lay
on the shoulders of the strong.
Today's challenge will show you
where in the tribe you belong.
'Can I go any further?'
You may have reasonable doubt,
but let your tribe down, tonight
your torch could go out."
>> We got tree mail, and it was
the one tree mail that's talking
about pure strength,
and I've got it.
I just, at this point,
hope to God I can use it.
It's totally my luck.
I hurt my ankle, and we think
we have a challenge
in a couple days, but we have it
the very next morning.
If I mess up today,
it's on my shoulders.
I want to win this challenge
more than I've wanted anything.
I want to carry this tribe
all the way
to the end of this game,
and I'm going to do anything
I can to do that.
>> PROBST: All right,
first things first.
Willard...
Take back immunity.
Immunity back up for grabs.
Before we get to the challenge,
I got to ask, Jeff--
you were hobbling in here.
What happened?
>> I rolled it last night
in the middle of the night
on a coconut, and heard a snap,
crackle, pop.
And I'm just trying to take care
of it right now the best I can.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready for today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: It is for immunity.
Here's how it works:
You're each going
to be wearing a belt.
That belt will be clipped
to a common rope,
so you will move together
as a tribe.
In addition,
you'll be carrying a backpack
with 20 pounds of sand in it.
Starting on opposite sides
of an oval course,
you will race, trying to catch
the other tribe.
If a tribe member gets tired,
and they want out, they can
opt out of the challenge,
but they have
to take their weight off
and give it to another
tribe member, then unclip.
So they're out of the challenge,
but the weight is still
in the challenge.
Somebody will have
to carry that burden.
First tribe to catch the other
tribe and touch one
of their tribe members
wins immunity--
doesn't go to Tribal Council.
For the losers,
somebody going home tonight.
Big enough stakes?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Koror, you still
have two extra members.
You're sitting two people out.
Who's sitting out?
>> Jenn and Janu.
>> PROBST: Jenn and Janu are
sitting out.
Everybody else, take your spots,
wait for my go.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Right away,
Jeff gets rid of his weight.
He's unclipping.
Can't run on that ankle.
Going to take strength
and strategy to win this.
>> Wait! Wait!
>> Faster, Caryn.
>> Wait!
>> Somebody's down.
>> PROBST: Caryn's down.
She gives her weight to Tom,
and she's unclipping.
Tom is now carrying 40 pounds.
Caryn is out of this
competition.
Ulong gaining some ground.
Willard's out of the race.
He gives his weight to Gregg.
>> I can't do it.
>> Give me the belt!
>> PROBST: Kim falls down.
She's out.
She gives her weight
to Bobby Jon.
He's now carrying
three backpacks.
Angie opts out.
James has her weight.
Ulong down to four members.
Koror with four members,
as Katie drops out.
Stephanie the only woman left
in this challenge.
It is very hot out.
Heat really taking its toll.
>> Coby, dig deep, will ya?
Come on!
>> PROBST: Walking through this
water, harder than it looks.
>> All right, here we go!
Pick it up!
Move!
Come on.
>> PROBST: Tom leading Koror
strong.
Gregg doing well.
Coby trying to keep up.
>> Yo, they're going to catch us
if we don't jog.
>> No they're not.
>> Yes they are, they're getting
close.
>> Look at Coby.
>> PROBST: Coby going to opt out
of this challenge.
Gives his weight to Ian.
Ian gives the weight to Tom.
Tom now carrying 60 pounds.
Tom, Ian and Gregg
against Ibrehem,
Bobby Jon, Steph and James.
Ulong trying to make a move
in a full-on sprint,
carrying a lot of weight.
Steph showing no signs
of slowing down.
All right, let's have a burst
or something.
No one's holding us back,
all right?
We hit the shallows, we dash.
>> Just think
of Tribal Council, guys.
We don't want to go.
>> PROBST: Koror trying to make
up a little ground each round.
>> Come on, guys!
>> Guys, they're getting closer.
>> James, give me
one of them bags.
>> Wear them down, guys!
Wear them down.
Come on. In front of me!
In front of me!
>> PROBST: James, giving another
bag away to Bobby Jon.
I'm good.
>> PROBST: Koror making up some
ground, closing that gap on
Ulong.
That kicks Ulong into gear.
>> Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
>> PROBST: Ibrehem winded.
>> Close, guys.
Come on.
>> They're wearing out.
Look at them-- they can't even
go through the shallows that
fast.
We can, so let's do it.
>> PROBST: Ulong really slowing
down.
James going to opt out
of this challenge.
Bobby Jon now with 80 pounds.
The longer this challenge goes,
the deeper the water is getting.
The tide is coming in.
We're down to three on three.
It's Tom, Gregg and Ian
for Koror.
Really closing the gap.
Ibrehem, Bobby Jon and Steph
for Ulong.
Ulong going to have
to kick it into gear.
Do they have anything left
in the tank?
Ulong's been to two
straight Tribal Councils.
Doesn't want to go back again.
>> I think we have to jog.
>> PROBST: Koror has yet to go
to Tribal Council, and
there's no rush to get there.
Koror making a move.
Bobby Jon now takes the lead.
>> Let's do it, guys.
Burst. Little burst.
>> PROBST: Koror is making up
ground in tiny increments,
closing the gap
slowly but surely.
Steph looking over her shoulder
as Koror gets closer and closer.
Does Ulong have anything left?
>> Go, guys! Koror! Whoo!
>> PROBST: Koror is making
a move.
Ulong very close to going back
to Tribal Council.
Immunity at stake!
Koror wins their third
Immunity Challenge in a row!
( cheering )
>> Koror!
>> PROBST: Koror, once again,
immunity going back to camp
with you guys.
No Tribal Council,
safe from another vote.
Ulong, sadly, you're getting
all too familiar
with Tribal Council.
Tonight, you will return
and vote out yet another member
from your tribe.
Head on back to camp.
>> All right, everybody,
I want to talk to all you guys.
First all, I think everybody
tried their heart out today.
I'm really sorry that
I couldn't help participate.
But I know there's no possible
way that I can get to the end
with a busted-up ankle,
especially in these conditions.
I know, myself, in three weeks,
my ankle may start
getting better.
>> Really?
>> In these conditions.
I'm not, I mean...
>> You don't even think,
like, a couple of days...?
>> To tell you the truth...
There's no way.
I can barely put
any weight on it right now
without clenching my teeth.
Like, every time I step,
I feel like a tear is going
to come out of my eye.
If I stay in here, you guys
aren't gonna get to the end.
>> I don't want you
to leave here, though,
and in two days your ankle
will be feeling fine
and us be like...
>> So we're going to vote out
someone else instead?
There's no reason to
vote off anybody else.
All right?
>> Yeah, we want you to stay.
>> Soon as we got back to the
beach, old Jeff said, "Guys,
you need to vote me off."
Oh, we were sad, you know.
We didn't want to vote him out.
He's strong, you know, he does a
lot around here, you know?
And the person we were planning
on voting out, which is Kim,
does hardly anything.
>> We vote Jeff off, it's going
to be like two people gone
anyway, 'cause she ain't did
none of the challenges.
She ain't do nothing
around the camp.
>> Yeah, she's down there laying
up, ain't doing nothing
down there.
>> She's so happy 'cause she
thinks she's okay tonight.
>> That boy's tough.
>> Yeah, I'd rather,
nurture him and feed him.
I feel very strongly
that Jeff should stay.
We should get rid
of Kim for sure tonight.
Jeff's weakness is our strength.
Even when he's down, he's ten
times stronger than Kim.
I'm definitely going to go talk
with other people in the tribe
and see what they think.
>> Bobby Jon, I don't
know about you,
but just to let you know,
I'm voting for Jeff.
>> You are?
>> Oh, yeah.
I planed on voting for Jeff
as soon as he hurt his ankle.
>> Okay.
>> And I'm not swaying from it.
>> Okay, cool.
Well, I ain't voting for him,
'cause I'm voting for Kim,
because I'll be danged
if I'm going to feed somebody
when they don't do nothing.
>> Yeah.
Some of the other tribe members
want to vote off Kim,
and I can see that
because she didn't really
do much, but I'm kind of hoping
once Jeff goes
she'll start maybe doing
a little bit more instead
of just thinking about Jeff.
>> Yes!
Check it.
Hey, I can cut them
right in half with one cut.
>> Watch this.
You watching?
>> What are they doing?
>> Come here, come here,
come here, come here.
Come here... come here!
>> What's he cutting, coconuts?
>> Just watch. Just watch.
Watch, watch.
>> Yes!
>> You're just doing it
to be a bad ass now.
>> Now I am. Heck, yeah.
>> She can't do that, okay?
>> Okay.
>> She's gone.
Or is he going?
Still tough?
>> Still tough.
We'll see.
>> Perfect day to leave.
Beautiful, warm.
>> We need you.
>> I know what you're saying,
but just let me enjoy this
one day.
>> It's not logical
to get rid of you.
I think you're afraid
that somebody else is going
to get voted off.
>> Huh?
>> Well, it is
right before Tribal,
and, of course, people
are whispering,
and I don't know what
conversations are taking place.
They could be all
be over there conspiring
and, "We're not
going to vote for him.
We'll see what his ankle does."
>> That's cool.
>> I think that's cool.
>> I'm feeling vulnerable.
I mean, there's no way of
telling what could happen.
I definitely think
there's a chance that
Jeff could be here tomorrow.
>> PROBST: You guys got to be
getting tired of seeing me here.
>> Oh, we're tired of it.
Very tired.
>> PROBST: Ibrehem.
Three immunity challenges,
three losses.
After tonight,
three tribe members gone.
Koror still
standing strong at nine.
Gotta be a little frustrating
to continually get pummeled
in these challenges.
>> Uh, it is very frustrating,
but honestly, today,
I know if we would have
had one person in there
who we really needed,
we would have won.
>> PROBST: You're saying
if you had Jeff
you'd have won the challenge?
>> I'm saying, if we would
have had Jeff, we would
have won the challenge.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon.
Jeff really
the difference in this?
>> No, he wasn't.
The difference was,
is-is Tom for Koror is what the
difference is.
He's a man.
He's a man among men,
and he single-handedly
whipped us, I think, today,
to be honest with you.
>> PROBST: Ibrehem, you're
shaking your head.
>> I don't think Tom
single-handedly beat us.
Him and his team did it
together.
We did good, but after
a while, you know, Bobby Jon
had 80 pounds on him.
We just needed that extra man,
and that's just point-blank
what it was.
>> PROBST: Steph.
How long after getting back
from the challenge
did the finger-pointing begin?
>> When we got back,
actually, Jeff sat us all down
and he just pretty much said
that he's really
hurting right now and he
doesn't know how much use
he's going to be to the tribe.
No one really got a chance
to point fingers.
He just gave us a lot to think
about coming into Tribal Council
tonight.
>> PROBST: Jeff, you got
the weirdest look on your face.
You're smiling.
>> You know what?
Jeff, I've always been a team
player my entire life, and I
really think that I screwed up
my ankle, and it was a deathful
thing for me as well as my team.
I'm not saying that we would've
have won today had I been there,
but I know that we would
have had a better chance.
That would have been 20 pounds
off one of these guys' backs.
>> PROBST: What's your point?
>> My point is that I want to be
able to help the tribe
in any way possible,
and at this point,
right this second, I can't.
I can't do anything.
>> PROBST: Ibrehem.
What are the other reasons
that you're starting to notice
about why you might
vote people out?
Is it to a point now where
you're starting to notice who
really is doing the work you
need versus who is starting to
say, "You know, we're okay.
I think I can take
a nap this afternoon"?
>> I think everybody works hard,
but sometimes
people might get a little tired
and might not want
to put in as much effort
as everybody else.
>> PROBST: But when it comes to
voting somebody out of the
game...
>> That can play
a big part in it.
That can play a big part,
in my opinion.
>> PROBST: Kim, you seem
very frustrated tonight.
>> It's not that I'm frustrated.
I mean, I'll admit to you, it's
it's hard being on this team
when you have these guys
that are super-strong and tons
of stamina and workaholics.
Like, I could never
measure up to Bobby Jon.
I mean, he's freaking Tarzan.
And it's frustrating losing.
I'm so sick of being here.
I'll be honest with you,
if he wasn't going home
then I would know
that I was one of the people
on the cutting block,
chopping block, whatever,
because our tribe's obviously
manifested itself to be a tribe
that the strongest stay
and the weakest go,
and it's not that I'm weaker
than the average person,
it just means in this tribe,
that might be where I fall.
>> PROBST: James.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: At any time today
was there any dilemma,
"Do we give him his wish
or do we keep him"?
>> Yeah, there's been a dilemma.
We've been debating all day long
on whether or not to keep Jeff
or let him have his way,
and we're probably
still debating.
It's just running through
our head, you know.
We don't even know what we're
going to do until we do it.
>> PROBST: Clearly this tribe
has not yet made up its mind.
Let's see which way
you're going to go.
It is time to vote.
James, you're up.
>> Kim... you are lazy.
You don't do anything.
You get out
of the race a day early.
You are not a helper.
>> You've become one
of my greatest friends
on this island.
I'm happy I got to know you, but
this is what you wanted,
so this what is I'm going to do.
>> Everything's fine, but
tonight I'm not going to play
you and Jeff's
little silly-ass game.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave
the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Jeff.
Two votes Jeff.
James.
Kim.
Two votes Jeff,
one vote James, one vote Kim.
Kim.
That's two votes Kim.
Two votes Jeff, one vote James.
Jeff.
We're three votes Jeff,
two votes Kim, one vote James.
I'll read the last vote.
Third person voted out
of Survivor: Palau.
Jeff.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Kill Koror.
>> PROBST: Jeff,
the tribe has spoken.
Time to go.
You had a tough
first eight days.
So the question is, how
do you turn tonight's vote
into something positive?
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
>> I've never lost this
bad in my entire life.
>> PROBST: Ulong gets desperate.
>> Don't freak out.
>> PROBST: And the tribes have a
big decision to make.
>> "Choose one tribal
representative
to make some important choices."
>> What if the person who goes
doesn't get to come back?
>> PROBST: You have not picked
a representative yet?
>> There is a huge part
of me that wishes
that I had not injured myself
to the point of being unable
to help my team
advance in the game,
and it was my choice,
and I know
that by making that choice,
my team is going to be able
to advance further
in the game.
Ulong, it's time
to take Koror to the cleaner.