>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> Everything I say you have
some snotty remark!
>> PROBST: Caryn and Katie went
head-to-head.
>> Get off me!
>> She's crazy.
She's completely lost it.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready.
At the reward challenge...
Go!
...as the tribes faced off
in hand-to-hand combat,
Koror took a beating...
Angie dunks Gregg!
...and Ulong dunked their way
to victory...
Ulong wins reward!
...winning material and a sewing
kit.
>> Ulong!
>> PROBST: Back at Ulong,
although morale was up...
>> That was so awesome.
>> We totally kicked their ass.
>> PROBST: ...Bobby Jon grew
frustrated.
>> I'm very disappointed with
my tribe right now.
>> Oh, so close.
>> Especially Kim.
I don't think she understands
the value of work.
>> PROBST: At Koror...
>> It's definitely a sea krait,
so be careful.
>> PROBST: ...the tribe tangled
with some deadly creatures.
>> That thing right there.
It's coming closer.
This is probably the stupidest
thing I've done in a while.
>> It's a game of survival and
we're going to get a shark.
>> Okay, here comes one.
>> PROBST: Before the immunity
challenge, Ulong faced a setback
when Jeff sprained his ankle.
>> It's totally my luck.
I hurt my ankle and we have
a challenge the very next
morning.
If I mess up today, it's on
my shoulders.
>> PROBST: Go!
Right away, Jeff's unclipping.
Jeff took no chances and bailed
out of the challenge, but after
a long test of strength and
endurance, it was Koror who
pulled through.
Koror wins their third immunity
challenge in a row.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Back at camp,
Jeff gathered his tribe.
I know there's no possible way
that I can get to the end
with a busted-up ankle.
If I stay in here, you guys
aren't going to get to the end.
>> PROBST: Some were not
convinced.
>> I feel very strongly
that Jeff should stay.
We should get rid of Kim
for sure.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Kim was spared when
the tribe honored Jeff's
wishes and voted him out.
Jeff, the tribe has spoken.
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I can't believe this is all
that's left.
We started out with,
like, so many people.
>> I know.
>> Tonight at Tribal Council,
Jeff went home.
I am very sad he's not here.
He's great for the team.
He's a great friend.
It absolutely is horrible to
lose the strongest player on
your tribe, but that's what
he had wanted, and so that's
what we did.
>> Koror is using strategy when
it comes to the immunity
challenge.
>> Yeah, but they're a
weak-ass team.
There's obviously something
going wrong because they're
not in shape and they're
kicking our asses.
>> We're not going to Tribal
again.
You guys understand me?
I'm going to stomp
anybody's ass that lags.
You know what I mean.
>> He means it in a good way,
though.
>> I don't know.
This tribe right now doesn't
have a lot of togetherness.
and closeness, like we thought
we had.
As it's built right now,
everybody's self-esteem's
getting down, but I'm hoping
we're going to turn it around.
I hope we do learn something,
but right now, I don't think
we have.
>> Tree mail.
Uh...
>> I knew it.
>> "Today you must choose one
and only one tribal
representative to make some
important choices.
The tribe will then have to
live with those decisions."
>> Katie and I went to go get
tree mail this morning and it
basically says the we need
to send a tribal representative
out, and that we have to live
with the decisions that we make.
>> We need to figure out
what it is.
It could be a person swap.
>> Yeah, or what if the person
goes doesn't get to come back?
>> I think Gregg should go.
>> I'm not crazy about it,
but I'm not opposed to it.
>> Everyone else is up for it?
>> I am.
>> I would definitely be willing
to go.
>> I would do it.
>> I'll speak right out
on that and do a vote.
Ian, you've made many good
decisions, you've been the
team leader here.
You want to go?
I say you go.
>> Yeah, he'd be good.
>> Today we were volunteering
on who wanted to go, me,
Caryn and Janu all volunteered.
But it's like nobody listened
to us.
They just said, "So, should it
be Gregg or should be it Ian?"
"I want to go."
"Well, should it be Gregg
or should it be Ian?"
"I want to go," I just kept
repeating myself.
>> I just don't want to lose
you.
>> I'll be back.
We'll see each other again.
Is that cool?
>> It's definitely
the tribe's vote.
Everybody seems to go for Ian.
I'm not going to fight for it.
By picking the team leader,
the separation of the group
is just obvious.
Katie, Jennifer, Gregg, Ian
and Tom are one unit,
so that makes five against four.
Once we saw them all band
together, it was obvious that
we're definitely the
underdogs here.
>> "Today you must choose one
and only one."
>> So somebody is going to be
the top dog here.
We represent you.
>> Hey, we're picking out of a
hat.
>> How do you feel about
doing it, Kim?
>> I'm fine with it.
I think you're good at it,
too, though.
>> Maybe we'll draw straws
or something.
>> I don't know.
I don't agree with the
drawing straws.
It seems like nobody likes
to sit down and think about it
for a second.
It's very impulsive, and I'm
sure that it won't be the best
decision once it's made.
>> Want to see what the
challenge is and then go from
there?
>> Yeah.
We have to go fishing right now.
Let's go.
>> Yeah, let's do that.
>> Let's go fishing.
>> There's a boat coming.
>> This is like some kind
of World War II thing.
>> It's on its way.
>> Oh, look at it.
>> PROBST: What's going on,
Koror?
>> Hey.
>> PROBST: Who's the
representative?
>> Ian.
>> PROBST: Ian, come on up.
>> Bye, Ian.
>> See you guys.
>> PROBST: All right, Ian,
for today's reward challenge,
your tribe is going to build
a bathroom, two sections:
a toilet area and a shower
and a wash area.
To help you build your bathroom,
we go to the Home Depot
toolshed.
(all exclaiming)
>> Oh, my God.
>> Who'd have thought I'd be
that excited to see tools?
>> PROBST: A few items.
You have a bush shower,
a shower curtain, some rings,
toilet seat, some twine, wire,
rope, lots of nails, right?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: In addition, timber,
and you get to pick six tools
from the toolshed-- six tools
that you will build your
bathroom with and six tools you
will keep for the remainder
of your time out here.
>> Jeff gave me the choice to
pick six tools out of
his toolbox.
It was a difficult decision.
But my dad owns
a construction company and I
grew up on a farm, so it
worked out okay.
>> PROBST: What's the last item
going to be?
>> It's going to be this one.
>> PROBST: All right, you have
one more decision.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: Koror now has three
extra members.
You're sitting three people out.
They cannot participate in the
planning or the execution
of this challenge.
Keep in mind, Ian, you cannot
sit the same people out in
back-to-back challenges.
>> Oh, that's right.
Okay, we have a immunity
challenge coming up, too.
Okay, so we're going to sit out
Jen, Coby, Janu.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Tomorrow morning, I'm going to
come back with a judge.
The person doing
the judging is Jesse.
He's got a degree
in Construction Management.
He's been with the show since
day one, and his team builds
all the challenges out here.
He knows what's possible
to be built out here.
For the winning tribe,
Jesse will come back
with our entire construction
department, and they will build
a shelter the likes of which
has never been seen.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Worth doing?
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: All right.
Get somebody to come help you
get all of your tools
and get to work.
>> Nice job, Ian.
>> Are we okay?
Yeah?
As far as my choices go, I hope
the tribe's happy with it,
but I'm feeling fantastic,
the adrenaline's running.
>> Good job, James.
Bigger than what we've
been getting.
>> We found Nemo.
>> PROBST: Ulong, come on in.
Good to see you guys
out here fishing.
>> We're trying.
>> We try.
We try.
>> PROBST: All right, so, the
reason I'm out here--
who's your representative?
>> Can we ask questions or no?
>> Can we ask you questions?
>> PROBST: You have not picked
a representative yet?
You guys don't have a leader.
You can't even pick
a representative.
Give me somebody.
>> James.
>> PROBST: James, get up here on
the barge.
>> You okay with that?
>> All right.
>> PROBST: James is worried.
>> I wasn't trying to be
the leader.
They picked me, but luckily
they did pick me
because if they didn't we
wouldn't have got
the tools we needed to build
our lavatory.
My stuff.
I used to build houses.
>> PROBST: So you've got a
background in construction.
>> I got a background.
This is hatchet with a hammer
on one end, hatchet
on the other.
>> Good choice, James.
>> PROBST: Okay, here's what's
what's going to happen.
Some of the guys from the
construction department
are going to build,
for the winning tribe,
the most kick-ass Survivor
shelter ever.
>> Oh, really?
>> PROBST: Sound good?
>> Hell yeah.
Leadership is not a role
I want to take on,
but when a reward challenge
is at stake, somebody's
got to step up and say,
"Hey, get up off your asses
and let's get to work."
>> The Koror construction crew
is in high gear.
We have a plan now, so we're
gonna pull all the stops out.
Koror is going nuts with this
thing.
>> Nice.
>> Got a nice pathway going.
>> Willard, we couldn't have
planned it better ourselves.
Look at that notch-- my God!
>> If you watch Tom and Ian,
they are very careful not to go
through the day without saying,
in front of the group, something
good about everybody in the
group.
>> Yeah.
>> I am carving "Watch your
step" to put before the walkway
to the latrine.
>> That's great.
>> Time for lunch and a team
meeting.
>> Tom is a leader.
That's what he does for
a living.
He's an officer in the
fire department.
He's highly motivated.
He works hard.
He's our little motor that
makes the train run.
>> Here we go.
Add water.
>> Every leader for every
project is always Tom.
That's the way it is
in this tribe.
Everyone is "Oh, Tom, oh, Tom.
Yes, Tom."
The women won't even throw
a stick in the fire without,
"Tom, Tom, can I throw a stick
in the fire, Tom?"
It's a little crazy.
>> Now, I'm taking a shower
and I want a little bit
of elbow room, you know,
so... 35 inches right here.
Mark it.
Big arrow.
Being the boss, it's a
big responsibility,
but I'm feeling pretty good
that I can take some skills
that I've learned and build us
a little outhouse, so we can
win us a shelter.
So measure from right there,
down there.
>> You look real funny right
now.
>> I do, don't I?
>> It's about 22.
>> 22 sounds good.
>> What if we laid them this way
because this is going to not be
real sturdy?
>> Oh, honey.
>> What?
>> We've got to nail it.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> It's going to be a frame.
I promise, it'll be sturdy.
Turn that back.
>> Sorry.
>> I'm happy to have James
as a team leader, but he can
be very fatherly, which can be
annoying at times.
Okay.
>> Okay, now...
Press, you understand?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> I use a staple gun
every day at my job.
It makes me mad that James is,
like, "Oh, do you need help
with that nail?"
Because I know what I'm doing.
When I have something broken
at my house I fix it.
Landlord don't fix it, I fix it.
>> What's wrong?
>> I'm really weak.
Like I need food.
And I know you guys need food,
but it seems you guys can go
better than I can without it.
Like I'm so dizzy I could
pass out right now.
>> What do you want to do?
>> I don't know.
>> Why don't you start taking
that shower curtain and sew on
"Ulong."
>> Kim's a little bit useless.
She's always trying
to get out of things.
Finally we found something she
likes to do, which is sew.
Something she can sit on
her ass, and...
But really, we've got five
people doing all the hard work.
Hey, Bobby Jon, I need some
trees about that big around.
>> When I started working
hard on something,
my whole body and soul
just goes into it,
every ounce of it.
You've got to want it,
you've got to want it
and that's what winners do,
winners keep fighting.
Champions keep persevering.
(grunting)
>> It sucks to be on a team
with completely "gung-ho,
I'll work until I die
and bleed to death"
type of people.
>> It's jammed.
>> Don't point that towards
your eyeball.
You want the honest truth?
I think I'm the smart one
sitting in the center of a bunch
of people running around with
their heads chopped off.
What are we doing about the
sink?
We need to get cracking.
We've got a lot of time now.
Let me tell y'all something,
that's why construction jobs
don't get done on time,
because people freak out.
Don't freak out.
>> James, he's going to end up
driving people insane
and I'm slowly watching
everybody mentally lose it,
so I'm kind of stepping back
and letting the beast
attack the beast.
>> Who wants to sit on the
potty?
We've got time for y'all
to try it out.
Get your asses over here.
Quit your whining.
>> Yes, the boat's coming.
>> Let's fall in, guys.
>> PROBST: Are you ready for us?
>> Yeah.
We're more than ready, Jeff.
More than ready.
>> PROBST: Koror, this is Jesse.
>> How you doing.
Welcome to Camp Koror.
>> PROBST: Jesse's our
production designer.
He's a tough judge.
>> We're a tough tribe.
We're okay.
>> PROBST: Good.
Let's go. Show us.
>> Tom, lead the way.
>> This morning Jesse and Jeff
Probst came to do the judging
so it was very nerve-wracking.
>> We have the path coming down,
it diverges.
We have a little sign here--
"Watch your step."
We'll take you over to the
latrine first, show you what
we've got there.
>> PROBST: Tom, you're a great
tour guide.
>> He is; he is.
>> I'll tell you a little bit
about some of the design
features-- we decided not to
enclose the walls.
>> Pretty good.
>> You can shake it.
>> Yeah, we notched out the
boards.
>> Got a newspaper?
>> We do have toilet paper.
You'll notice that we have...
>> It's not the stinging tree,
is it?
>> No, it's not.
>> The tour was terrific.
It was taking them through
our thought process, how we
worked and how we came up with
what we came up with.
I'm very confident.
I'd be surprised if we didn't
win and we need this.
We have Rat City, USA.
And we need a shelter.
>> Yeah, let's have a look
at the shower.
All right.
I like the path, a nice touch.
>> We mounted the actual shower
above the tree, and you're
able to adjust it
to whatever size
you want to go.
You want a demonstration?
>> Yeah.
>> I think I'm the dirtiest kid
in camp, so...
Hand me the soap, will ya?
>> PROBST: You got everything
you need?
>> Yeah, I think I'm pretty
good.
That's good.
Thanks very much.
>> No problem.
>> PROBST: So here's the deal,
guys: Jesse's is going to judge
you based on creativity
and functionality.
If he decides that
your bathroom is the best...
you'll know it.
We'll return.
Fair enough?
>> Fair enough.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: See you guys.
>> Might see you guys soon.
>> I think we put everything
that we had into this challenge,
more so than any other
challenge.
If I'm judging facial
expression, I think Jesse was
very impressed.
I don't think there's any way
we can lose this one.
>> Ulong.
>> Here he comes.
>> Uh-oh.
Hurry.
They didn't even see it.
>> They didn't even see it.
>> Hurry, hurry.
They're right here now.
>> That's it-- stop.
>> Right here.
>> Put the shovel up.
Put the shovel up.
>> PROBST: Looks like you guys
are still working.
This is Jesse Jensen--
he's the guy I told you about.
You want to give him
a tour or you want him
just to look around?
James is going to do that.
>> You ready for a tour, buddy?
>> I'm ready for a tour.
"For a good time
call Jeff Probst."
(all laughing)
>> PROBST: I hope you got the
right number down.
>> Yeah.
>> We've got our wash basins,
we've got a vase,
got a toothbrush holder.
>> Those your toothbrushes?
>> Yes. I haven't used it yet,
but they have.
I don't brush my teeth
because I'm a redneck.
>> You tend to bite down.
>> We've got our shower right
here and we have a drain.
>> Nice.
>> Surprisingly, our bathroom
area and everything looks
really good.
It's a lot nicer than we thought
it would ever be.
>> Let's have a look around
the back.
>> All these posts can be dug
up.
>> We figured it didn't matter
if you saw through here, because
you're washing your hands.
>> PROBST: Seen enough?
>> Yeah, I've seen enough. Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, so here's
how it'll work, guys: If Jesse
decides your bathroom is the
best bathroom we will return
with our construction crew.
If we're not here by sundown,
pretty good idea we're
not coming back.
>> Fair enough.
>> Thanks, everybody.
>> Thanks for the tour.
>> PROBST: See you later.
>> Good job, James.
Really good job.
>> You did it.
>> You did so good.
>> Everybody did it.
I think we won, no doubt.
Look at it.
It's perfect.
They'll be back in about...
I estimate two, three hours.
>> How long do we have to wait?
>> I think like an hour,
hour-and-a-half.
>> If nothing else works out,
we have a shower and a toilet.
Good effort.
The Koror construction crew did
a fantastic job on this
challenge, so we're really
proud.
But you never know what
rabbit Ulong is going to pull
out of their hat.
>> Is that a boat coming?
>> I hear something.
>> A boat.
>> Oh, yeah.
It looks like a Home Depot boat.
>> Yeah!
(cheering)
Yeah!
>> All right!
Yeah, bring it!
>> Oh, my g...
>> Yeah!
Yes!
>> Come on, cartwheels
down the beach!
(cheering)
The barge boat came around
the corner again.
We could see the Home Depot
sign on it, and there was a lot
of, lot of joy in camp.
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, we're going
to sleep good tonight.
>> We totally deserve this.
>> Bring it home.
>> Yeah.
>> I knew it.
>> Yes!
>> They'll be back.
>> I don't know, man.
I'm kind of thinking that
we may have lost.
Still trying to keep hope up
because the sun hasn't set
all the way.
It's not dark yet,
but it's looking kind of grim.
(hammer pounding, saw buzzing)
>> Instead, we get
a construction crew.
Like, come on.
We have a new shelter going on,
so, uh...
so a good day for Koror,
for sure.
Everything worked out the way
it's supposed to.
Oh, it's a frickin' palace.
It's like the Taj Mahal.
It's fantastic.
Gosh, thank you so much.
>> No problem.
You're welcome.
>> It's fantastic.
>> I can't even begin to explain
how great our shelter is--
it's beautiful.
It's not even a shelter,
it's a home.
We've got a hammock in there
and a lantern, and they
built us a picnic table
and, like, a little platform
for us to just hang out on.
It makes the quality of life
here so much better.
>> We got something else here
for you, a little housewarming.
>> Oh...!
>> What is it?
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
>> To you guys, thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Oh, this feels so good.
>> Thanks a lot, guys.
Awesome. Thank you.
Thank you.
>> As if the shelter wasn't
enough, these wonderful people
turned around and gave us
a housewarming gift,
and it was a crate with two
bottles of ice-cold champagne
in it.
We don't even know
if it was the alcohol,
but it was the most delicious
thing you ever tasted
and it felt great.
I'm not that light yet.
(giggling)
>> Caryn?
(cackling)
>> I guess the other team won.
>> I don't get it.
Damn.
>> Probably just because
they haven't won one yet.
>> No.
That's B.S.
>> Yeah, it is.
It seems that we lost
the challenge.
I was confident that
we had it, you know?
We worked hard.
It looks good.
It's a shame.
But that's all right,
'cause it just makes us
more angry that we lost.
We're ticked off,
so we're going after them
and we're going to run right
them like a dang bulldozer.
They won the first three times,
it was their time.
It's our time now.
>> Yo!
We got tree mail.
>> Oh, my God, it's
a gladiator thing.
We're going to have to hit
each other off beams.
>> That's what I'm thinking.
>> "Square off in a circle
against your opponents.
Balance and strength:
two crucial components.
David beat Goliath
using brains over brawn.
Be the one to lose this one,
you could be the next gone."
We're going to all have to
take on one person with that.
>> Oh, yeah, that's what
it's going to be.
>> I'm going to practice
a little bit.
I hate for things
to come down to the wire,
but it seems like
it has with us.
I mean, this next immunity
can make or break us.
If we don't get it, we're down
to five and they have nine.
We can't lose another
tribe member.
>> We're going to be like
wolverines.
>> All I know to do to win
this next immunity challenge
is just to fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight.
That's all I know to do.
You've got to block out the past
and worry about right now.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Katie...
Immunity back up for grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
tribe members will engage
one-on-one in a sumo-style
battle on a platform.
Using large padded bags,
you will attempt to knock
your opponent off the platform.
Two rules-- you got to keep two
hands on the bag at all times.
You cannot use your feet
as a weapon.
First tribe to six wins
immunity.
Koror, because you have
three extra members, you're
sitting three people out.
And because this is men versus
men, women versus women,
you have to sit out
two men and one woman
to even up the tribes.
Who's sitting out?
>> I am.
>> PROBST: Ian, Katie, Willard,
sit out.
Everybody else runs.
Take your spots.
Wait for my go.
All right, first round,
man versus man--
it is Tom for Koror
and Bobby Jon for Ulong.
>> Here we go, Bobby.
>> Come on, Tom.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready.
Go!
(yelling, cheering)
Both guys going strong.
Tom is down.
Bobby Jon pushing.
>> Come on, Bobby! Go!
Come on, Bobby!
>> Push! Push!
>> PROBST: Tom back up.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Tom pushes Bobby Jon
in.
Koror scores the first point.
>> Yeah!
(cheering)
>> PROBST: East coast versus
west; Steph versus Jenn.
>> Go, Jenn.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready.
Go.
Jenn comes on strong, but...
Steph not budging,
and pushes Jenn off easily.
We're tied one-one.
Gregg versus Ibrehem.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Ibrehem with a big reach
advantage.
>> Yes!
(cheering)
>> PROBST: Both hands on the
bag, Ibrehem.
>> Throw him off balance, Gregg!
>> PROBST: Gregg pushing hard.
Ibrehem lost his bag.
Ibrehem's in.
(cheering)
>> Gregg!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Koror leads two-one.
Angie versus Caryn.
Survivors ready.
Go.
>> There you go!
Push her off that way!
>> PROBST: Angie makes the first
move, she's pushing.
Caryn's on the edge,
and she's in.
Angie wins.
We're tied two-two.
James versus Coby.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Coby comes out strong.
James is in!
Coby wins.
Koror leads three-two.
First tribe to six
wins immunity.
Kim versus Janu.
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> Come on, Kim,
Come on, Kim!
>> There you go!
(yells)
>> PROBST: Kim makes the first
move, but it backfires.
Kim is in.
Janu wins!
Koror leads four-two.
Got a rematch.
Bobby Jon versus Tom.
Tom won the first round.
Survivors ready.
>> Come on, Tarzan!
>> PROBST: Go!
Bobby Jon coming on strong
again.
Tom fighting back,
Bobby Jon's in!
(groans, cheering)
Tom wins again!
Koror leads five-two.
We have a rematch.
Steph versus Jenn.
Last time Steph won--
different stakes this time.
Jenn wins, Koror wins
their fourth straight immunity.
Come on, you got it, babe.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Steph comes on first.
Jenn pushing back hard.
Steph has to stay alive,
or Ulong's out.
(indistinct shouts)
Come on, Steph!
Jenn wins this,
they win immunity.
(shouting)
>> Go! Go!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Jenn fighting back.
Steph pushing hard.
She comes on strong,
knocks Jenn down.
She's back on her feet!
Jenn back down again.
Scraping those knees
but not giving up.
Steph pushing harder.
And Jenn is in!
Steph wins.
Ulong stays alive.
Koror leads five-three.
A victory by Gregg
wins immunity for Koror.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Ibrehem with a big push!
Gregg is in!
Ulong stays alive.
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Ulong continues to
fight back.
Koror now leads five-four.
It's another rematch:
Angie versus Caryn.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Angie wasting no time.
Caryn's in!
Ulong has battled back,
five-five tie!
>> We're not going back
to immunity!
>> PROBST: Angie's so excited,
Tribal Council!
Angie's so excited, she doesn't
know what to say.
>> Take that and see how it
feels!
>> PROBST: It comes down to
this.
We are tied at five-five.
James versus Coby--
immunity at stake.
Winner of this match claims
victory for his tribe.
Survivors ready.
Go!
James comes on strong
out of the gate.
Coby fighting back.
Using that height.
>> Come on, Coby!
>> PROBST: That reach has got
James going backwards.
He's got James down.
>> Coby, yeah!
>> PROBST: Pushing him.
James fighting back,
squirreling around.
Coby still on it.
James recovers; now he's got
Coby down.
>> Go, Coby, go!
>> PROBST: Coby still pushing.
James on the edge.
>> Get him, James!
Come on, James!
(indistinct shouting)
>> Come on, James!
>> PROBST: Coby trying to push
him over with his shoulder!
And he's got him!
James is in!
Koror wins their fourth straight
immunity challenge!
(whoops)
(yells)
Koror.
For the fourth time.
No Tribal Council tonight.
Nobody going home for this
tribe-- staying strong at nine.
Ulong-- nothing to say.
Four straight visits
to Tribal Council.
This tribe of six will become
five tonight.
Head on back to camp.
>> I thought we would have
it today.
>> Me, too.
>> I didn't know Coby was that
much stronger than James.
>> Feels terrible to have my
butt whooped by a homosexual,
you know, but a lot of gay folks
are strong, man.
They all working out at the
gym and all, you know.
Damn.
>> We got our butts kicked
today.
Imagine that.
That's what's been
happening here lately.
I personally got my butt
whipped, and now we got to go
to Council tonight and we
got to vote somebody off.
>> I am so sick of losing,
I don't know what to do.
I've never lost
this bad my entire life.
I'm about to flip out.
When we got back
from the challenge,
I was so mad and upset
and embarrassed and just pissed
because James lost it for
all of us.
We could have won immunity,
and there it was out of our
hands again, four in a row.
We lost.
I'm friggin' embarrassed.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm mortified.
>> Well, at least we know
that we're doing our part.
>> Right.
>> We didn't fall off.
>> Angie and I, we did the best
we could do.
We won both our heats,
so thank God for the women,
'cause the guys, they're
getting their butts handed
to them.
>> Hey, Kim.
>> What?
>> Tonight, we ain't playing
the game.
We ain't even going
to talk about it.
We're just gonna go write
a name down, you know.
We all know whose name's
going down.
>> I'm laying right here in
the shade.
>> Kim, she sits on her butt,
but that's it, you know.
She don't do nothing.
She might drink some
coconut juice, you know.
That's about the most work
she will do, you know.
Come on.
So she's gone.
>> James told me, don't talk
about your vote.
Like, if anybody else had
said it, it would have been
fine, but ever since then,
it just makes me cry.
>> If you get voted off,
it's going to be three guys
versus two girls.
And they're just going to vote
the girls off, one-by-one.
Kim, she knows she can be the
next one to go.
Everybody is completely
fed up with her.
But if we vote Kim out,
and three guys and two girls,
Angie and I are in big trouble.
I don't even know what to do.
>> Kick all the guys off.
I think the girls
definitely see the value
of us sticking together,
and I would more than be
willing to see some of these
guys go because they aren't
the greatest.
>> It's a slam dunk for me, man.
Kim, I just think she's
not a very strong girl,
so I just think it's smarter
to vote off the weakest link.
Way to go, man.
>> They're just going to totally
take us out.
>> Yeah.
>> So what are we going to do?
>> Well, I just feel like
we need to take control.
>> Me and Steph are definitely
talking about trying to vote
trying to vote one of the guys
out instead of Kim.
We'd have the upper hand,
but then again, we might just
lose another immunity challenge
because she's not pulling
her weight, so what's the lesser
of two evils?
Trying to keep somebody around
and hope you may not get voted
off, but if she helps us lose
it, then-- pfft!-- you know,
somebody's going anyways.
>> The tide's never up this
high-- what the hell?
>> It could go either way.
I could go or one
of the guys could go
because this is a group
that actually won't make
final decisions till it's time
to pick up that pen and write
down the name.
>> PROBST: I saved your seats
for you from last time.
>> Appreciate it.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
some of the facts.
Seven challenges,
you've lost five of them.
Steph, how frustrating is it
for you to continue to get beat?
>> It's so frustrating.
I feel like I've never lost
this much in my life.
Like, I don't know whether
to scream, flip out, cry...
I mean, I feel like we are
giving it our best and it's
not enough.
Or at least I know I am
and it's, it's killing me.
>> PROBST: Angie?
>> I was really, really upset
we didn't win that reward
challenge for that shelter,
and then, on top of it,
to lose, like, you know,
the next immunity challenge.
Oh, man, it's just devastating.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, I don't
think we've ever had a tribe
lose this many in a row.
>> Right.
Yeah, things aren't good.
Yeah, we're, we're bad.
Right now, we're down.
Obviously, you know what?
I'm not doing something right,
and I mean, I consider my head
being on the chopping block,
if you want to know the truth,
'cause I have let our tribe
down in the challenges,
and I know I have and there's no
excuse for that, bottom line.
>> PROBST: Okay, tonight, we're
going to talk about
accountability.
It is time to get to the bottom
of what is wrong with this
tribe, starting with camp life.
Kim.
Is there one person
that goes fishing?
Two people?
Does everybody do it?
>> We all go out, but it seems
that Bobby Jon and James take
the Hawaiian sling
the most and go.
>> PROBST: When's the last time
you went fishing?
>> We all go out together.
We don't go into the water
and fish.
>> PROBST: So what are you
doing?
>> We sit on the boat.
>> PROBST: Well, how useful is
that?
>> I mean, Stephenie and I
couldn't just row out there
all the way into the deep blue
and go fishing and turn
around and row back in.
I mean, you might have
to send a search team out.
>> PROBST: Steph, if you had no
men in this tribe, could you
guys survive?
Are you self-sufficient as
women or are you relying
on these guys?
>> I think we rely on them,
but I think we could be
self-sufficient if we had to be.
>> I'm not sure if the guys
think that us women are as
wieldy with things like the
machete and axes and the spear.
Like, when we were
working on our reward
challenge, people were
trying to help me nail-- now,
I nail a lot at home, okay?
I know how to hammer a nail,
it's not hard.
But the guys think we're
a little bit more delicate
than we really are.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon.
Is that fair to say?
>> You know, I've only been out
here 11 days, and I've learned
that these women right here
are just as strong or more
stronger than men.
If Kim can use that sling
and go and kill us a bear,
I mean, I want her to.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's challenge.
James.
Frustrating to lose to Coby?
>> No doubt.
I'm thinking, "Man,
he's a hairdresser.
He don't look like he's
got any muscle tone, I ought
to be able to whoop him."
I tell you what, that boy
right there has got some
ass behind him.
>> PROBST: Well, of course
you're going to say that...
>> Whooped my ass! Yeah!
>> PROBST: Today it took
six points to win.
Five of their six points
came from beating the men.
The women carried
this tribe again.
>> Yes, they did.
>> PROBST: Kim, today you
may have lost, but as a whole,
the women...
>> Were stronger.
>> PROBST: The women kept you
guys in the challenge today.
>> Yeah, definitely.
If we had had stronger guys
with a burning passion
and control with that passion
we would not be here right now.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Ibrehem, you're up.
>> Kim, you're a good girl, but
you're just not putting much
effort into the tribe lately.
Sorry.
>> My vote is for James.
James, just wary of dictating
a little too much.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Kim.
James.
One vote Kim, one vote James.
Kim.
Two votes Kim.
One vote James.
Kim.
That's three votes Kim.
Fourth person voted out
of Survivor: Palau--
Kim.
That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> Bye, Kim.
>> PROBST: Kim, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
After a demoralizing first
11 days, the question is,
what are you going to do
to change the outcome?
Grab your torches, head back
to camp.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
While Gregg and Jen get cozy
at Koror...
>> They're gonna think we're
stupid if we can't tell
that they're together.
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
>> PROBST: ...the Ulong tribe
gets lost.
>> Do you know the way
to get back there?
>> No.
>> I'm trying.
Don't get down my throat.
>> PROBST: And the game takes
an incredible turn.
>> I had a lot of fun
playing Survivor.
I wish it had lasted quite a bit
longer, but, unfortunately,
I guess tonight was my night
to go.
I hope the girls really
stick up for themselves,
because Lord knows, the guys
have proven that they're
nothing special on our tribe,
and I really hope that, in the
end, somebody from Ulong wins,
and not somebody from Koror.