>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> This is the scariest thing
and the hardest thing thing
that I'll ever do.
>> PROBST: The last Ulong member
battled to survive alone.
>> I feel like I'm going
to starve to death.
No, no, no. Man!
It's tough.
But if I win...
it'll be worth it.
>> PROBST: As she reached
her breaking point...
>> Oh, my God!
PROBST: ...Stephenie received
some good news.
>> It's a merge!
I'm going to have friends!
And food!
>> PROBST: She packed her
things...
>> See you later, Ulong.
>> PROBST: ...and paddled out
to join Koror.
>> Oh, God, here she comes.
>> Oh, my God...
>> PROBST: Koror welcomed
their new tribe mate
with open arms.
But some had different ideas.
>> As much as I'd like
to have her around,
I think she needs to go
really fast.
>> PROBST: Two Palauan fishermen
arrive to teach the tribe how to
fish.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: And then they
celebrated with an island feast.
>> Where's Tom?
Drinking from the bottle.
( woman gasps )
>> PROBST: And some celebrated
more than others.
( gasps )
>> You all right?
>> Yeah, I'm good.
>> Stephenie?
>> PROBST: The next day,
Coby told Stephenie
all of the tribe's
secrets and alliances...
>> Jennifer is your
main bout right now.
Because Jennifer is
so jealous of you.
>> PROBST: ...irritating some of
the other tribe members.
>> It is so obvious
what he's doing right now.
Coby told Steph that Jenn wants
to take her out,
which isn't good.
>> You're not the dead man
walking.
>> PROBST: Tom reassured
Stephenie that their alliance
from day one was still solid.
>> You have friends in this
tribe who are going
to keep you alive.
>> Donuts!
>> PROBST: At the first
individual immunity challenge...
15 chocolate chip cookies.
>> Oh, me, me.
PROBST: ...the tribe succumbed
one-by-one to temptation...
...leaving Tom as
the last man standing.
Tom wins the first
individual immunity!
( cheering and applause )
At Tribal Council,
Janu seemed ready to go.
>> I think it's me tonight.
>> But it was Coby's loose
lips...
Tenth person voted out
of Survivor Palau...
...that cost him the game...
Coby, the tribe has spoken.
...making him the first
member of the jury.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> What are we at, 25?
>> 25 it is.
>> Last night, Coby got voted
off, and I was taken by
surprise-- I had no words, I
couldn't even say good-bye to
him, I just...
felt...
this huge loss.
I was so taken aback,
I felt betrayed.
Nobody had informed me
of anything.
>> I'm sorry, are we
at summer camp?
We're on Survivor.
This is not necessarily
our true colors.
We're playing a game.
>> Exactly.
>> What was that performance?
>> I don't know.
>> I know, like,
her eyes and, like, I...
seriously, the smile looked
like a jack-o'-lantern to me
Janu is completely mad.
She's crazy.
She's a crazy person.
Last night at Tribal Council,
she was sitting like
a jack-in-the-box
with this really creepy smile
and eyes on her face.
She was just so excited.
>> She was excited.
She thought she was going.
>> It was scary.
I don't like it at all.
It freaked me out.
It was like a clown.
>> Katie started...
she was gossiping about Janu.
She was saying,
"Ooh, Janu is giving looks.
Janu is making faces."
And... Janu overheard it.
>> What are we,
junior high, Katie?
We pretend
we're all good friends?
It's-It's silly.
Do you understand what I mean?
I have nothing against you
personally,
'cause I don't know you.
>> I have nothing against you.
>> But you're being...
>> You're being creepy.
I'm sorry.
>> Well, then why don't you
tell me to my face?
Why do you have to go to your
little friends and tell them?
That's what I don't understand.
>> I'm sorry. I...
>> No, you don't have to be...
you don't have to be sorry.
>> I'm telling you that I am.
>> That's who you are.
>> I apologize.
That wasn't fair.
>> I'm not used to playing
games.
If I had something to say about
you, I swear to God, I would
come up and say it to your face.
Why do I have to go to...?
"And she did this."
'Cause you're
Saturday Night Live?
'Cause you're the
comedian-to-be?
>> She just talks in these
circles and doesn't make any
sense, and then she's like,
and, you know, "Katie, then
you're making fun of me,"
and she does the face again,
which is even more scary
when she's impersonating herself
being impersonated.
>> I am very upset.
>> Okay, I apologized, Janu.
So if you can't get over that,
then that's...
>> It doesn't matter
if I can or not.
You're done.
You're done with
the conversation.
>> I-I just don't want
it to turn into,
like, you know... you're
off in a corner, because...
>> It's going to turn into
whatever it's going to turn
into, 'cause all you guys are
going to turn on each other.
It's fine.
>> Janu is turning it into
just something that we need to
kind of put up with out here.
It's kind of a buzz kill
to have her around.
It's unfortunate, but...
what are you going to do?
I'm not going to vote someone
out because I don't like them.
I can get over it.
She plays a bigger role
in all of our strategies,
where Stephenie
only threatens it.
Some may think that Stephenie
deserves to stay around, but in
the grand scheme of things,
winning this game
is hardly about deserving.
I don't care if someone
deserves to be here or not.
If you have a role
in my strategy,
then you deserve to be here
so you can help me win
a million dollars.
>> PROBST: Ready for today's
reward challenge?
>> Mm-hmm. Yes.
>> PROBST: Okay, for today's
challenge, you are going to
build a tower in the water.
Here's how it will work:
We will randomly divide
into two tribes of four.
Using a buoy for assistance,
you will transport
the six pieces of scaffolding
one at a time into the water,
and construct your tower.
Once you've built the tower
and it's secure,
one tribe member will climb
to the top, grab the small flag,
and race back to the beach.
First tribe of four
to get back to the map
with their flag wins reward.
Want to know what
you're playing for?
( Survivors murmuring )
The winning foursome
will leave here and take part
in a Palauan feast.
( chuckling )
You'll be met by the high chief
of this area at a bai,
which, in case you're wondering,
is a traditional meeting house
where chiefs get together
to work out tribal politics.
You will drink local beer,
you will also have food
and dessert.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: All right.
We will randomly divide into
two tribes and we'll get going.
All right, the tribes
are Steph, Ian, Katie and Jenn
taking on Gregg, Tom,
Janu and Caryn.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors, ready...
Go!
Dead even heading out with
the first piece of scaffolding
and finding out it is not
as easy as it looks.
Those pieces weigh
30 pounds each.
>> Over here, it's over here.
>> PROBST: Tom and Gregg going
down for their tribe.
Janu and Caryn sitting this out,
letting Gregg and Tom
do the work.
Ian, Jenn, Steph, and Katie
all working together.
A lot easier with four people
than it is with two.
>> My side's on.
>> Mine's not on.
Caryn and Janu
still sitting this out,
letting Gregg and Tom do the
work for their tribe, while all
four members of the other tribe
are working together.
Those pieces are going to need
to line up exactly before they
will fit together.
Janu goes out to help.
Tom, Janu, Caryn and Gregg
have their first piece
of scaffolding in.
They're heading back
for their next.
Ian, Jenn, Katie, Steph
has their first piece in.
They're heading back, trailing.
Tom and Gregg, Janu and Caryn
coming back with their second
piece of scaffolding.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Ian, Steph, Jenn,
Katie coming back with their
second piece of scaffolding.
Janu and Caryn resting again
with the platform.
Now Janu heading out to help,
just as Ian, Jenn, Katie, Steph
start to assemble
their second piece.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Tom, Gregg, Caryn,
Janu have their second piece
of scaffolding.
They're heading back.
>> One, two, three.
Ian, Jenn, Katie, Steph
has their second piece in.
Heading back,
trying to make up some time.
Four pieces left.
>> Let's go!
Come on! Run, run!
( indistinct shouting )
>> PROBST: Katie really
slowing down her tribe.
>> We've still got it.
>> Push with me, go in front.
>> PROBST: Tom, Janu, Gregg and
Caryn with their third piece
of scaffolding.
>> Come on, guys!
>> Grab the...
>> Grab the thing.
>> Katie, pull.
>> Katie, help us!
>> Katie, pull this!
>> PROBST: Everybody wants to
eat.
Big feast.
>> The other way.
>> Gregg trying to get
that last corner on.
They have their third piece,
heading back to shore
for another one.
Ian, Steph, Jenn, Katie
working together.
They have it--
they're heading back in!
>> Here! Let go...
>> PROBST: Janu starting to
struggle, trying to get to the
platform to hold on.
Janu gets a second wind,
she goes back underwater again.
Gregg getting into a position
where they can hand him
that fourth
piece of scaffolding.
Ian's group making up some time.
Gregg and Tom are lined up.
Janu is lined up.
They have their fourth piece
of scaffolding.
Steph, Ian, Jenn, Katie
have their fourth piece in,
and they're heading back.
They have two pieces left now.
>> Everyone, let's get it.
>> PROBST: You can only move as
quickly as your slowest member.
Tom, Gregg, Janu and Caryn
are worn out.
>> Guys, only... couple of
yards-- you got it.
>> But they still manage
to get that fifth piece.
Ian and Steph not quitting.
>> Pick it up! Push it over.
Come on, Steph!
>> PROBST: Tom, Gregg, Caryn,
Janu have one piece left.
Katie has hers.
Heading back
for their last piece.
You guys are still in this.
Tom, Caryn, Gregg, Janu, coming
back with their final piece
of scaffolding.
Tom and Gregg, Janu and Caryn
starting to wear down.
Steph, Ian, Jenn, Katie
not quitting.
Gregg, Tom, Janu, Caryn
with their final piece
of scaffolding.
Once they have the cap on,
they'll grab the flag,
heading back to the beach.
Jenn, Steph, and Ian doing
all the work.
Katie's worn out.
Tom, Janu, Gregg have
the final piece on.
Janu's going to climb
to the top.
( grunts )
Janu unclipping her flag.
Now it's a race
back to the beach.
Janu is back.
She's waiting
on the rest of her tribe.
Janu, Tom, Caryn, Gregg...
win reward!
Palauan feast!
( cheering and gasping )
>> That was good.
>> PROBST: Ian, Jenn, Katie,
Steph... great effort...
just not enough.
So I got nothing for you.
Head on back to camp.
You guys ready to eat?
>> Yeah, let's do it.
>> PROBST: Get your stuff.
Head on out.
>> Hello.
>> Hello!
>> Welcome!
( speaks native language )
>> We've been in Palau now, um,
for weeks and weeks, and
really have seen nothing
but the wilderness of Palau.
( singing in native language )
This was my opportunity
to meet the people.
It's so good to be here.
>> Please accept
our little gift.
To be respected by them and
then to return that respect.
It's just another gift
that I bring home.
>> It's a privilege,
an honor to present you
our little gift.
>> Thank you so very much.
I've never been in the presence
of a real chief.
He gave me a beautiful
headpiece with flowers
and he blessed me.
I was very, very moved.
( women singing
in native language )
>> We were just very thankful
for the opportunity to
step outside of life on the
island here and experience
what is life in Palau
really like.
( singing in native language )
>> Oh, wow.
>> Beautiful.
>> We sat down at a little table
very low to the ground
with pillows
on which they just started
a procession
of epicurean delights.
Oh, my gosh.
>> What's that, chicken?
>> Chicken or turkey or
something.
Oh, my gosh!
Barbecue.
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> Corn on the cob, guys.
There was no talking
game strategy, planning,
we left all of the game
and strategy at the door.
>> Thank you.
>> I think I'm going
to make myself sick.
Halfway through the meal, I had
to get up and excuse myself.
I thought I was going to have
an embolism.
( retching )
>> Yup, she is.
>> Thank you.
>> You know, it's kind
of disappointing,
you get this big meal in you
and we're all enjoying it
and want to... want to take down
as much as possible,
and, you know,
there's four other people
that would have enjoyed it
a ton, but unfortunately,
Janu just couldn't handle
the entire thing.
( burping )
>> Hey.
Can we tell you a dinner story?
>> Yeah, I want to hear
all about it.
Well, I'll tell you what we got.
They rolled out,
I mean, we had a fish.
It was a regular salad.
>> What kind of dressing?
>> Squeezed lime on it.
What else?
>> Barbecued ribs.
>> Barbecued ribs?
>> Chicken.
>> Chicken, corn.
>> Corn?!
>> We didn't even talk about if
we had brought back any food.
We knew they were assuming that
we didn't bring back any food,
and Gregg says,
"Okay, don't finish your stew.
Don't eat another bite."
Don't, uh... don't fill
yourselves up too much.
Don't full yourselves
up too much.
>> Why?
>> 'Cause we brought
some back for you.
>> No, you didn't.
>> You did not!
( screaming, laughing )
>> What is that?
>> You'll have to wait for that.
>> They're like, little donut
holes.
>> They're like a sponge cake.
>> Oh.
>> Oh, yummy.
>> What is it?
>> Mostly chicken.
>> It's meat and stuff.
>> It's grub, grub.
>> Here's chicken.
>> Oh, my God.
You guys, you are the best.
Oh, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
>> You're welcome.
Happy Thanksgiving.
>> I love it.
>> Whatever that is,
it's the best.
>> I know.
>> The yellow...?
>> Go for it.
>> You guys didn't have this?
>> We just came back
from this feast,
and Janu says, "Oh, I want
to try just one more,"
and reaches out
and takes some of the food.
>> It came out in this, like...
>> I thought it was interesting
that Janu decided to say,
"Oh, you know, I didn't get
to try that."
'Cause she was vomiting
or whatever,
and she stuck her hands
in there, and ate our dessert.
Actually, Caryn did it, too.
But, you know,
what are we going to say?
"Get your hands off
something that you brought us?"
I don't think so.
>> What's it look like,
anything?
>> Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
>> What's an "Oh, my God?"
>> Look at that.
>> Oh, boy.
>> Oh!
"Feeling claustrophobic?
Are you prone to worry?
Panic during this one,
you could be the next
to join the jury."
( gasps )
What is this?
>> Oh, man this is like...
>> It's a cage underwater.
>> ...get out of the cage kind
of-- underwater?
>> Underwater?
You have to put it underwater
right away?
>> I bet you... I'll bet you.
"Feeling claustrophobic?"
Oh, yeah, underwater.
>> I definitely need immunity,
because apparently
I'm the "strongest" girl,
and I'm just as much of a threat
as any of the guys.
But we'll see, I mean, I'm
doing the best I can out
here, and I just hope
that I can get immunity.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Tom.
Immunity is back up for grabs.
Today's immunity challenge is
going to test your ability
to remain calm and not panic
when everything else
in your body says otherwise.
You all take a spot in the
water, underneath
a grated steel barrier.
As the tide begins to rise,
the water will rise,
and your breathing room
will slowly decrease
until you run out
of breathing room.
The person who stays
in this challenge the longest
wins immunity,
guaranteed a one-in-seven shot
at a million bucks
and the title of sole survivor.
One more thing:
Today's challenge also reveals
how you handle fear.
The first person to bail
on this challenge
will face the ultimate
test of fear:
You'll be taken to a new beach
and abandoned there tonight
to live on your own.
You'll have flint and steel,
you'll have a machete, you'll
have a jerry can full of water,
and you'll have some
fishing gear.
So if you've learned anything
in your first 26 days out here,
you should be fine.
If not, it's going to be
a miserable night.
Make sense?
Take a spot out in the water.
We'll get started.
>> Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Begin.
>> This man walks into a bar.
( laughs )
>> He's got a bar in one hand
and a bar in the other.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: First person out,
leaving here on a boat,
taken to an island,
abandoned...
>> I'm thinking of stepping
out just to get away from this
crowd for a night, Jeff.
( laughter )
>> That'd be great.
>> A little vacation
from the tribe.
>> Get away from the rats
for a night.
>> That's right.
>> PROBST: Jenn, think you'd be
all right on your own?
>> I think it'd be
kind of tough, actually.
>> PROBST: How about you, Janu?
>> I would try my best.
I don't, I'm already
getting cold in here,
so I don't know how long...
What's gonna be worse?
>> PROBST: Which would be worse,
hanging in that water cold
or being left alone tonight?
>> Probably hanging in this
water cold right now.
>> PROBST: Are you starting
to panic a little?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Just like that,
Janu's out.
( laughter )
What just happened, Janu?
Was it me saying
the word "panic"?
Janu... how are you at fire?
>> Uh, I don't know.
I'll find out tonight.
>> PROBST: Have you made fire
yet?
>> Um, no.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Katie, glad it's her
and not you?
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Doesn't seem like a
lot of love lost with these
guys.
They don't seem too concerned
about you tonight.
>> That's not true.
>> Not true at all.
>> That is not true, Jeff.
>> PROBST: You know what?
I'm sitting here asking her if
she knows how to make fire,
and you guys are making jokes
like you're at open mic.
You tell me,
what am I supposed to think?
Water starting to rise.
Soon, you will run
out of room completely.
This challenge has been going
for about 40 minutes.
This is where mind over matter
comes into play.
The water's completely covering
everybody's ears.
Now it's starting to creep up
toward the mouth and the eyes.
Caryn opts out
of the competition.
We are down to six.
Water really creeping up
toward the mouth and eyes now.
Jenn almost underwater.
Steph partially underwater.
Ian struggling.
Pushing his face
through that grate.
Jenn is underwater.
Will she come back up?
Katie's out of the competition.
Jenn still underwater.
Steph goes underwater.
Both remaining women are running
out of breathing room.
Ian goes underwater.
Jenn and Steph still underwater.
Ian's back up.
Jenn is out of the competition.
Steph is out of the competition.
We are down to three--
Tom, Gregg and Ian.
All five women are
out of the competition.
Immunity at stake.
Water coming in over the eyes,
into the mouth.
Gregg goes underwater.
Gregg is out of the competition.
>> Good job, Gregg.
>> PROBST: Tom trying to create
a hand snorkel.
Ian plugging his nose.
>> I can't believe they're
still up like that.
>> PROBST: Immunity at stake,
safety at Tribal Council.
That's it!
Tom wins immunity!
( applause )
>> Good job, Tom.
>> Was it me?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Okay, some business
to take care of.
First of all, Janu,
we're gonna bring your boat in.
You will be taken
to a deserted island.
You'll be left on your own
with the materials you have.
>> Be well, Janu.
We'll see you tomorrow.
>> Good luck, Janu.
>> Janu, good luck.
>> PROBST: Tom... immunity--
come over and get it.
Once again, you are safe
from the vote at tomorrow
night's Tribal Council.
For the rest of you, including
Janu, somebody else is
going to be voted out of this
game; you'll become the second
member of the jury.
Swim on back to your boat.
>> Right now, I am
going to a different island,
all by myself,
because I couldn't finish out
the immunity challenge.
I don't think that I'll be
scared as long as I have fire.
I think if I am going to be
in the dark,
then I think I'll get
a little bit more scared.
This is very hard,
and it's very frustrating,
but I don't want to give up.
I just feel very inadequate,
'cause I see the fire come up
and then... it goes away.
And I try to put little
pieces... and it's not working.
Ow!
This is a challenge for me,
but I needed time
away from that camp.
I'm not getting along well
with anybody.
I feel very much on my own,
and... it is me against them.
Woo!
I've got fire.
Yesterday, I didn't even
want to be here, but maybe God
was just telling me,
hold on a little bit more
because this is the feeling
you are supposed to get.
So who knows?
Every day brings new
experiences, and right now,
I am probably the happiest that
I have been in these 26 days,
'cause it's all about me
and this little island.
It's mine.
It's all mine.
The moon, the stars,
the water...
and my fire.
It's all mine!
>> The big decision that we're
facing right now is
who's going home tonight?
>> Who we, uh...
Who we thinking today?
And my thought with that is that
that's like an emotional
response because they get along
with Stephenie, and Stephenie
has the ability to form
some inside bonds early.
No one's going to do that with
Janu, and so I know I could
convince Jenn that
Stephenie's the one.
>> From day two, Katie, Ian,
myself and Stephenie had all
decided that we'd try
to run this as a final four,
and we all agreed that
should we get split
into different tribes,
every man for himself,
but look out for each other
when we do get back together.
The problem with that right now
is Jenn and Gregg,
who have since joined Ian,
Katie, and I, and have become
five, are adamant
that Stephenie goes home.
So at what point do we stop
rewarding Janu with, um...
>> We're the only ones here,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
I still struggle with the
question of why, why not now,
if then, you know?
I mean, then why for the same
exact reason why wouldn't...?
>> Well, I think Stephenie
is a bigger threat than Janu.
>> And there's no way that Janu
squeaks by in the end?
>> If she wants...
I mean, she wants
to go home so bad...
>> Well...
we know they have to go.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That's true.
I'd-I'd get concerned
about the whole eleven Tribal
Councils in a row, and
Stephenie is still surviving.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I just feel like
it's a story developing
that we need to put an end to.
Stephenie is a physical threat.
She's a competitor.
She's got a strong will.
She wants to win this game.
There's other folks, like Janu,
who don't want to win this game
as much as her.
Stephenie's story has been
continuing and continuing,
so you can just see it
all coming together.
Stephenie conquers Ulong, then
comes in and conquers Koror,
and we want to all prevent
that from happening.
>> I love her to death.
I'm really going to miss her.
But...
>> Right.
>> Better now, than she
getting too comfortable.
>> Yeah.
>> As things seem now
within the tribe,
Stephenie appears
to be going home tonight.
So, it's not...
where my heart is,
but anything can happen.
>> How you doing?
>> Hey! How was it?
>> Did she say it was great?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, she said...
>> Tell us about it.
Um... It took me about two and
a half hours to make a fire.
>> You got it?
>> You got fire?
>> You got fire.
>> Good for you!
>> Good job.
>> Three hours.
>> You did it. You did it.
>> Do you feel better?
>> You seem like
you feel better?
>> Better? Um...
Yeah. It was, uh...
full-circle for me.
It was... it was great
to be away from here, and it
was great to be on my own.
And I just had time to be by
myself, and that was good.
>> Wow. That's amazing.
>> Good job.
>> Good for you.
> Congratulations.
>> Well done. Well done.
>> To be honest, I didn't want
to come back here,
and when I got here,
everybody was like,
"Oh, that's great. Hey, good
job. Way to go."
The same people that were being
rude and saying that I
created animosity.
Just... not... nice.
>> I mean, we all agreed that it
was Janu tonight,
and Janu wants it to be her,
but for some reason I have
a feeling it's me.
Today, there was never a time
when I could grab anybody alone
and walk down the beach.
>> We'll see.
>> Yeah, that's the plan.
Who-- you?
>> It almost seems like no one
wants to talk about it,
so I'm really nervous.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring
in the first member of the jury.
Coby, voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
Janu, let's talk
about your night alone.
You were abandoned
on a separate island
with meager supplies.
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: How'd you do?
>> I did great.
I, um, finally got the fire
going, and then, um,
did a little dance.
It was really exciting.
>> PROBST: Yeah, that...
That had to be a-a big
accomplishment for you.
>> It was a very big
accomplishment, and I tried to
put myself to sleep, and in
the morning, the sun rose,
and it was a whole new day.
It was great.
>> PROBST: As you left in your
boat, everybody waved
and said good luck.
Did you buy it?
>> Um, honestly, Jeff,
it-it was, um...
No.
I'm sure that half of it was
sincere, but the other half
was, as they call it, the game.
And when I came home today
from the island, it...
it just felt really strange.
It felt like I didn't belong.
>> PROBST: Caryn, you look like
you're counting
to ten over there.
I'm just shocked.
You know, if that's the way
she chooses to take it,
that's-that's...
that's in Janu's head.
>> PROBST: Tom, at this point
in the game, is it worth
versus threat-- who deserves
to stay in this game,
versus who can't I beat?
>> Yeah, well, it's all
gamesmanship now.
Nobody is voting
based on, uh, who they like
or who makes me laugh.
The game is on, and people
are basing their votes
on how it positions them
in the game.
And eliminating competition
is part of this game.
>> PROBST: Gregg, same question.
>> It's... it's not a question
of worthiness,
and I think threat, you know?
Everyone that wants
to win the $1 million here
is a threat to me.
I mean, you definitely want
someone in the game
who is not going to really try
than you would someone who
is giving five million percent.
And some plans have been
established, and some
people may be threats within
those plans.
Unfortunately, you know,
Survivor isn't
always about fairness
and who deserves what.
>> PROBST: Katie, why keep you?
>> Why keep me?
>> PROBST: Yeah.
>> Well, I don't
pose any threat at this point.
Especially as far
as challenges go.
>> PROBST: Janu, why keep you?
>> No reason.
They can get rid of me.
>> PROBST: There's no reason
they should keep you?
>> No, because, I mean,
I have to be honest.
I had a really rocky road so,
if I was them, God, I'd be sick
of myself already.
>> PROBST: You almost seem like
you want to go home.
>> It doesn't matter, Jeff.
Whatever happens, happens.
I'm... I'm completely satisfied.
>> PROBST: Is there a part of
you that wants to say "Vote me
out"?
>> Yes. Absolutely.
But I don't know what they'll
do.
>> PROBST: Ian, why keep
somebody who's saying, "I want
out of this game.
I'm not going back to camp"?
>> Well, if you feel
like you don't want
to continue in this game--
if you feel like, you know, you
want to set your torch down--
then you have the
power to do that.
You have the ability and the
power to set your torch down at
any time, and there's nobody
keeping you here.
>> PROBST: Stephenie, if looks
could kill, Janu would be on the
ground.
>> It's just... it's just...
it's nothing against Janu.
This... It... it kills me.
I can't even...
Someone who I feel, like,
could care less
if they're even here.
( crying )
And here I am, like...
I'd kill to be here.
>> Yeah, but... what you need
to understand from my point is
that I already received what I
needed to receive
from this whole experience.
>> And you're fine with that.
>> Yes.
>> You could care less if you
leave right now, right?
>> Yes. That's... that's
correct.
>> I care. I...
I'm not done playing
this game and, like,
if someone asked me to
vote them out, see ya, because
you don't deserve to be here.
( sniffles )
And I'm...
>> PROBST: So you feel you're
on the hot seat tonight?
>> I know I am.
It's just... it's not that.
It just... it kills me
that someone who wants
to basically go home that bad,
these people will keep around
just because...
I don't know why.
I guess I showed too much heart
and too much will.
>> PROBST: Tom, in your
profession, unity, camaraderie--
big part of it.
When you hear somebody like that
laying it out, and you have
somebody next to them
who's saying,
"Please get rid of me,"
is there a dilemma for you?
>> There is a dilemma.
Um... Stephenie would fit into
a 108 truck in a moment, and,
uh, everybody in the company
would be proud to work with her.
And it's... it's not work,
and it's not camaraderie.
It's Survivor.
So there's a huge
difference here.
>> PROBST: Janu, if you had your
way, what would happen tonight?
>> I would ask the tribe to vote
me out and keep Stephenie in.
>> PROBST: What's the difference
between you
laying your torch down,
and you looking to this group
and saying, "Vote me out"?
>> I guess, after reflecting,
and, um, understanding this,
there would be no difference.
So I would be willing to lay
down my torch so that Stephenie
can have a chance
to stay in the game.
>> Not just for me.
If she wants to lay down her
torch and she wants to quit this
game, she can do it, but...
not on my account.
>> Do you want me to rephrase
it?
What I am saying
is, I will lay down my torch,
and I don't want Stephenie
to feel that I am doing
it for her.
That's something
that I have to do.
>> PROBST: I just want
to be clear.
You are, on your own,
quitting this game?
>> Yes, Jeff.
I will lay down
my torch this evening.
>> PROBST: Well, I don't
know if it's appropriate.
We have rain coming down.
Maybe this is your final
epiphany or cleansing moment.
I see that you brought
all your belongings.
Go ahead and gather them,
bring your torch over.
Janu, per your wishes, this game
is over for you, but you will
not go home.
You'll return and be a part
of our jury.
Thank you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Good night.
Another strange turn of events
at Tribal Council.
Steph, you've hung in there
for a long time, overcome
a lot of odds.
You escaped another one tonight.
Sounds like you have your work
cut out for you.
Grab your torches, guys.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Tom might have
to be the next to go.
>> PROBST: Stephenie steps up
her game.
>> I'll do it,
if you guys are game.
>> PROBST: And one of the men
could take the fall.
>> We didn't vote Stephenie out
when we should have, which is
the first round.
You want to think I'm a threat?
I'll show you
how threatening I am.
>> I asked them to please let me
go home, and it didn't work,
so I made the last move,
and I decided to take myself
out of the game.
I guess I did make
a major power play, and I guess
I did ruin their plans.
Even though I laid down my
torch, no one will ever be able
to take away this most
unforgettable experience.
No one.