>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> I was pissed at you.
You cost us the game.
>> PROBST: James and Ibrehem
squared off after Tribal
Council.
>> If you was listening,
I said I dove down.
I was at two bottles.
>> All we know is,
you went down three times,
didn't come up with a bottle.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, it was Stephenie's
sharp shooting that carried
Ulong to a much-needed win.
Ulong wins reward!
( cheering )
>> We won!
>> PROBST: Ulong savored their
triumph.
>> From here on out--
>> We win.
We needed this to boost
our spirits and morale,
and basically,
it was a whole new
chapter for us.
Ready?
>> PROBST: ...and enjoyed a
once-in-a-lifetime experience
at Jellyfish Lake.
>> They're just all just coming
at you.
It's just kind of like a
euphoric type of feeling,
and I just kind of wanted
to cherish every second
'cause I was
at a place in this world
where I won't ever go again.
>> PROBST: At Koror, a violent
storm raged...
>> You awake?
This isn't going to go anywhere.
There's no way.
>> PROBST: ... causing Janu to
question the strength of her
will.
>> It's so hard.
>> It is hard.
>> And I'm so depleted.
>> Janu is losing it.
She gets totally
caught up in her head
And I think she's grating on
everybody's nerves a little bit.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Koror has their rope undone,
pulling it up.
...Ulong's comeback
proved to be only temporary.
Koror wins their fifth straight
immunity challenge!
Back at camp,
Stephenie and Bobby Jon
hatched a plan to ensure their
safety at Tribal Council.
>> I'll vote for James with you.
>> Right.
>> That's only if you
promise if the three
of us are still here,
you and I go to the end.
No, we'll go to the end.
And we'll vote Ib off.
He wanted to make an alliance
with me that I vote
for James tonight.
He wants to vote
Ibrehem out next.
I really don't know
where I stand right now.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Stephenie voted for
Ibrehem, causing a tie vote.
Two votes Ibrehem,
two votes James.
Steph, Bobby Jon,
you will vote.
It's your last chance
to change your vote.
But when the second round
of votes came in,
Stephenie had changed her vote.
The seventh person voted
out of Survivor: Palau.
And James took the fall.
Sorry.
I had to.
>> PROBST: James, the tribe has
spoken.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> How many people do they have?
Eight.
And we're down to three.
So they're still up
in numbers, but
sometimes the best
finish, you know?
The people in last
always turn around,
like a second-half team, almost.
I mean, it can happen.
I mean, the odds
aren't in our favor, but...
>> I mean, it just feels weird.
Like three people are left.
It feels like
so long ago when we had nine.
I'm really surprised.
I mean, I thought I had
this all figured out,
and now having our tribe, Ulong,
lose every single
immunity challenge--
I'm completely
shocked and surprised,
and I'm embarrassed.
I wish we could have won,
but everything
happens for a reason.
I know I did the best I could.
>> This is kind
of weird, the situation.
Have you ever spent this
much time with people?
>> No.
>> The same group of people?
>> Day in, day out.
>> No. Not my boyfriend...
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> Not my fam...
not even people I love.
>> It was definitely weird
trying to feel like
a tribe when you're down
to three freakin' people.
It does almost feel
almost like a group of friends
rather than a tribe.
If we had to go
to Tribal again,
I think it would probably
be very, very emotional.
>> Like, let's just
bring on the merge.
Let's just do it.
>> Yeah.
I have a feeling
that that's going to happen.
>> We're down to three people,
and Koror, they have eight,
and I don't know, maybe it's
meant to happen like this.
Maybe this is going
to get me, Stephenie and Bobby
further in the game
than we expected.
Maybe in some kind of weird way,
this is gonna pan out and work
out in a, in a good way for us.
>> Yeah, I'm, I'm pretty, I'm
happy with our decision last
night.
>> I think it was right.
I mean, you got
to make alliances
some time or another,
or you won't even...
>> I know.
I think it's beneficial.
Bobby Jon had
approached me yesterday
and said, you know, that
he thought that we could
go far together as a team,
and I feel that I can trust him
a lot more than
I can trust Ibrehem.
And I feel that we have
a strong alliance.
Ib is a good...
He's a good contender, too.
I just don't see myself
going real far with him.
I just think that we're going
to be real safe together.
I think we'll go far together.
>> Mm-hmm.
You got to do
what you got to do.
>> I was going to say,
do you see Tom doing crunches?
>> It tried to eat me.
It could have.
Be careful.
There's a lot
of meat in there
>> Whoa.
>> Holy cow.
>> Ian comes out
with the biggest clam.
It was like
"The Birth of Venus."
It was the biggest clam
you've ever seen.
You could stand inside of it.
It seriously looked like it
weighed like a hundred pounds.
>> It's probably older
than you, Ian.
>> Probably.
>> Older and heavier.
>> One...
>> Get your hand in there.
>> ...two...
three!
I got the clam, thinking,
"Okay, look at me,"
like keeping
the role of the provider.
>> Clambake.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I'd say we probably had
six or seven pounds of meat,
so everybody had
almost a half a pound of meat.
That's more meat
than we've had at any meal.
>> Mm-mm.
>> So we just kind of set the
big clamshells out by the shore.
There was still a lot of blood
left over from the clam.
So we were just kind of
kicking it by the table.
>> And all of a sudden,
somebody sees a shark.
>> Oh, there it is!
That's not bad--
Right there.
>> Ian and I both jumped,
grabbed the spears,
and jumped in the water
ready to get him,
and, and they're quick.
You know,
they take off right away.
Let's sit back for a bit
and then run in.
>> Look at that one.
>> Where?
>> Oh, dude.
With the nail?
I had to go to jump the boat
and I cut my foot open.
So I was kind of disabled.
And then, everybody saw Tom
running down the beach.
>> Tom, out of nowhere,
he caught a shark.
( Gregg laughing )
>> How did you get it?
>> I hit with it the machete
and cut it in half!
Whoo!
( laughing )
Look at that!
How's that for a shot?
>> Watch it, watch it, watch it.
>> It was one of the most
amazing things
I've ever seen for-- especially
for a, a city boy
from, from New York.
>> And wham!
>> He's a madman.
>> Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about!
Oh... is that me?
>> How's that feel?
>> How did you get that?
>> Whoo!
>> Oh, my God.
>> That's intense.
>> He just jumped
in the water and stabbed it.
>> I whacked him.
He started thrashing around.
I jumped on him,
worked down to his tail
and then just pulled him out.
>> You're a madman.
>> Geez!
You try to be the provider.
All you're trying do is bring
in enough food for the tribe,
and then somebody
has to come along
and one-up the hell out of you.
>> The adrenaline is leaving
now; I'm scared.
What did I just do?
>> I got a big giant clam
and then Tom came back
and got the shark.
So, next, I guess, the next step
for me is to get,
like, a humpback whale
or something and bring it in.
>> Tom, that was
one of the most unbelievable
things I think I've ever seen.
>> I say, he keeps one-upping
me.
>> ( whoops )
>> The cat's out of the bag
that I'm a strong player
and I'm fit and I'm not
the oldest guy on the tribe.
I would think the butcher
wrapped it, huh?
With a little butcher
string and stuff.
You can't go back
and, and now pretend
that you're less than you are
or that you're--
you know, don't have
capabilities.
It's kind of done.
Unbelievable.
>> Mm-hmm.
That's good.
Here, I'm grabbing...
Oh, now who's the great white
shark killer?
>> I seriously don't think
I can eat any more.
>> So we had all this meat.
Everybody was all excited, so
Tom went to here
catching the shark.
And so it's like, "Oh..."
The second he caught it,
me and Gregg both
looked at each other and went,
"Hmm. It's going to be a lot
harder to vote him off now."
You know, you can only
taunt me so long
before I strike back at you.
>> Hmm.
>> ( imitates bottle
popping open )
What have we got here?
Want to read it?
>> "You're lost in the wild.
There's no one around.
"You find yourself thinking
you'll never be found.
"Use all your resources,
"'cause when push
comes to shove,
"build a signal on your beach
to be seen from above.
"Then a plane will fly by
and within the next hour.
"If your signal's the best,
he'll drop supplies to devour.
>> "So put your brains together.
"You can use only three.
"Creativity will reign
victorious.
Which tribe will it be?"
So we have to build
some sort of signal.
>> We have to build a signal.
>> Something you can
see from the air.
>> I say we burn our friggin'
shelter, our old shelter.
>> I can knock that
bathroom down
and y'all can burn
all that lumber.
>> We got tree mail telling us
to build a signal
that is very creative,
that could be seen
from the air.
There's going to be a plane
that's going to fly over
and decide whether our signal
is better or whether Koror's
signal is better.
It's going to drop a load of
supplies and goods to devour.
We really need it.
We could use the food
and we could use
the, the just, morale boost.
>> So we're going to do "Ulong"
in fire?
>> Each of us get on like an end
and start lighting
the ends, you know?
>> Let's just gather as
many as we can now,
start the fire,
and then we can continue
to feed the fire in
the form of Ulong.
>> Yeah.
>> While those three are
doing this,
the rest of them are
going and getting
food and water and stuff.
We don't win,
we're going to have to go
get food after this.
>> It's all good.
>> You know what I mean?
Oh, yeah, it's all good.
I'm just saying.
That's what stinks about
being down in numbers.
>> We've been tearing apart
our old shelter
to use for this challenge.
We've been cutting bamboo and
using part of our bathroom.
We've used everything we can.
We really want to win this.
I'm sure the other tribe's
doing pretty good.
They've been doing pretty good
at everything else.
So I'm not underestimating
them one bit.
So far it seems like they have
a lot of smart people.
So we're just going to see
if work can overtake smartness
right now.
>> "So put your brains together.
You can use only three.
"Creativity will reign
victorious.
Which tribe will it be?"
>> We can use only three people.
Who wants to perform?
>> I'd like to perform.
You want to be a team?
>> I'll do it, too.
I can do it.
I'll be in.
So who, me, Katie and Caryn?
>> I'd like to do it.
>> Go to it.
Make us proud.
>> The message said we had to do
an SOS, and only three people
could participate.
So through long talks and
discussion ,it turned out to be
Gregg, Caryn and Katie.
Which I actually think
is a good choice,
because Katie is very creative.
Caryn is a hard worker and
then Gregg's got the muscle.
>> Start bringing all
the bamboo down?
>> Yep.
>> We'll get the frame and
we'll get that stuff down?
>> Yep.
>> The first thing we wanted to
do is find the right location.
We're a little shortchanged
in terms of shoreline
back at camp.
So first thing we did was moved
our location
halfway down the beach,
which just getting our materials
there was a lot of work.
>> This is a tough challenge.
This is really...
It's high 80s, low 90s.
It's tough to stay hydrated
and refreshed when the sun is
beating down on you,
and we're working in the sun
because we want to be
in an open stretch of sand
where the plane can see us.
A boat in the water, right?
We don't have a beach.
It's a problem.
It's nerve-racking.
I'm sitting here like a cat
on a hot tin roof.
You want to be a part
of this thing.
You just want to help.
There's a lot on the line.
There's nothing you can do,
but be an observer.
And I don't like the position.
There's a lot of apprehension
from where I'm sitting.
>> Okay, so the idea is
to get as much attention
from above as possible.
So we're using bamboo
and coconut
to outline our letters,
which is "Got food?"
It's a great question.
We're making two big fire
bundles right here
that we're going to light
right when they get there
to get some black smoke going.
We're gonna see if the rope
soaked in kerosene works.
I think that would be a great
thing if we can use that
because that would be something
they wouldn't have.
>> It works, yeah.
Works good.
>> It's getting late, huh?
>> Yeah.
>> I just hope they don't wait
too late to start the fire.
So much hinges
on that fire, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> How are you going to make
sure that stays lit?
If you're careful at first,
once it's lit, it'll
join in the hoopla.
>> Hoopla.
>> PROBST: All right, Bob,
Here's the setup.
Both tribes were given
instruction to build an SOS
That would be visible
from the air.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Your job as a
certified drop master,
check out both camps
and judge which one
is, in fact, most visible.
You ready to give it a go?
>> Let's go have a look.
>> PROBST: All right,
head over to Ulong.
>> Here he comes.
>> ( yelling )
>> PROBST: All right, Bob,
you had a chance
to look at Ulong's camp.
Give me your assessment.
>> Well, if you're not flying
right over the top of it,
it's very hard to see.
It's stuck way back
into the forest.
But it was big, it was visible,
It's not bad for three people.
>> PROBST: Head out to Koror.
>> How is it coming?
>> Don't worry about me, guys.
>> Here they come!
Come on, Caryn.
>> Get ready, Caryn.
It's working.
>> There's the plane.
>> Yep, here comes the plane.
>> Coming from here,
I don't see any
smoke or anything.
>> Yeah, I don't see any sm...
You can see it from here.
I don't see any smoke.
We could see what
they were doing from here.
I didn't see any smoke at all.
And almost their whole plan
was fire.
So my fear, I think, might have
come to truth
that I don't know if they got
the fire lit.
I think the odds are against
us, to be honest.
>> PROBST: All right, Bob, give
me your assessment
over Koror's SOS.
>> Well, Koror's SOS--
it was creative,
it was bigger,
but the big thing was it was set
down off the beach,
which makes it more visible.
>> PROBST: You're the judge in
this. Do you have enough
information to make a decision?
>> Yes, I do.
>> PROBST: Let's set up
for the drop.
( cheering )
>> I'm so glad for you guys!
>> I'm so happy!
I'm so happy!
>> Sweet, guys!
Sweet!
>> Brains over brawn once again.
>> That's right.
>> Ooh!
( cheering, applauding,
laughing )
>> In the box was three bottles
of red wine...
>> Cheese tortellini
and tomato sauce.
>> And then we had all of these
military food packages
that you could heat up
and eat as meals.
>> Fishing line.
We also got a bunch
of fishing equipment,
so we're going to take
our fishing life
or camp life up to the next
level now.
>> "Meals ready to eat."
>> Just like in the army.
You put it in and
that's how you heat it.
>> Wow, cool! Chicken,
spaghetti with meat sauce.
( cork pops )
>> Anyone want to give
the toast?
>> I'm just, I'm...
To a great tribe.
Our tribe really worked
together well.
We are like a well-oiled
machine.
>> For believing in us to win.
>> Thanks for believing in us.
>> We win a lot of challenges
for a reason.
I mean, it doesn't happen
by accident.
Peanut butter.
>> How good is that?
>> Poor Ulong.
There's three of them now.
I don't know how they can
maintain camp,
compete in challenges
and stay mentally strong.
I think they must just be
absolutely beat up over this.
( airplane approaching )
>> Here it comes.
>> I'm not sure what's going on
here.
Ours?
They coming to us?
Stop, stop.
>> Please!
>> Stop, stop...
>> Oh, that's so mean
if they don't drop here.
>> What are they doing?!
>> Oh, my God, no!
>> I guess we lost
the reward challenge
because the plane flew by
and didn't drop anything.
We worked hard on it.
>> I guess they worked harder.
>> Or I'm sure they worked
smarter, knowing them.
>> We thought we won.
>> Gregg and Jenn-- they joke
about it, about him
being the make-out bandit
and they kiss and blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
So I guess they think
they're dating.
I don't know.
I don't really care.
As long as I can get them
on my side and my vote.
>> Going once?
>> Where you going, Jenn?
>> She's going to get water.
I'll go with you, Jenn.
Should I put on my date clothes?
>> Between Jenn and I,
we're a strong alliance,
but when we're talking,
I can't really have
a great conversation with her
'cause I'm, like,
are people looking at us?
How are they reading
this conversation?
People are going to be, like,
all right, they're talking
strategy.
They're going to be suspicious.
They're not going to trust us.
Me?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Really?
>> It's tough because
I am playing a game.
It's tough for me to play a game
and be, like, a good date,
you know?
I can easily get sidetracked
by women.
So I'm making a conscious effort
to play things cool.
Jenn felt I was just starting
to be kind of standoffish.
Because we had
you know, kicked things off
really well
and it was kind of exciting.
But then you kind of get into
the context of the game
and realize, you know,
that's your priority.
>> Mm-hmm.
I like Gregg a lot
and I think he likes me a lot.
But Gregg is very intensely
focused on this game.
It's all he can think about.
So there have been days
where he's very off to me,
and it's been kind of strange.
You know, until we spoke,
I didn't know
what was going on.
You know, I didn't know if he
was still, if he was still
in the same place,
if we're just going
to be that alliance,
but there is still
a romantic connection.
It's still there.
We'll just see if he can,
he can loosen up a bit.
>> I'm concerned with Gregg
and Jenn because they are tight,
you know?
What is going to happen
when all of a sudden
we have to tell Gregg or Jenn
that the other one
may be getting voted off
that night?
You're bringing in a whole
different volatile emotion
that is separate from this game.
So, uh, I'm, I'm concerned.
We're all watching
the relationship
and seeing where
the alliances lie.
The little romance or whatever
they've got blossoming,
it just could be
a monkey wrench
that we don't see coming.
>> Got a clam?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Way to go, boy.
>> Good job!
>> Damn.
>> Bobby Jon was able to catch
a pretty large clam,
and a nice little hand-sized
black fish.
Oh, man, when he got that fish,
we were all super excited.
>> Good, isn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, we got something.
>> Yeah. Good job!
>> Gosh, hitting that fish felt
like making an extra point,
you know, to win the game
or something like that.
I felt like, like I had scored,
you know.
It felt nice.
I think that fish done.
>> I'm just going to try
to cut him up.
>> Finally we were able
to get some protein
in our bodies.
We ate the clam.
We ate the fish and we ate
I don't know how many pans
of coconut, so, you know,
we got protein, we got carbs,
we got everything.
>> I think it's pretty damn
good.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, I feel the protein.
The meal was good.
I mean, it was nice to be full
for a change.
I definitely think the food
will help us in a challenge
if we get one.
Oh, cool.
>> "The way to lose this one
is to be just plain lazy.
>> BOTH: "Don't think you need
to practice?
"Then you're just crazy.
>> "To keep your tribe together,
slot the pieces into place.
>> Got to heed this warning or
you could be out of the race."
>> Yeah, immunity.
That's supposed to be a star.
>> Yeah, it's supposed
to look just like that.
Okay, cool.
Let's go sit down.
>> Let's go sit down
and do it.
>> We just got tree mail,
we have an immunity challenge,
and something
to do with a puzzle.
And if we don't get it
together,
one of our tribe members
could be going home.
Sliding them around.
This got to go up somehow,
it's got to go...
>> We always keep the faith.
We haven't won one yet.
Maybe today will be different.
We're ready.
We're full.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
What's going on, Koror?
We now bring in Ulong.
James voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
>> James!
You ain't lying.
>> ( mimics James ): Come on.
>> PROBST: And then there were
three.
How's the fishing going, Ulong?
>> We got a little hand-sized
little black fish.
Finally.
I'm just scared
to death of sharks, so I'm just
trying to get over all that.
>> PROBST: How about for you,
Koror, any luck with fishing?
>> We're doing okay.
>> Yeah, the beast master
came out
and Tom battled a shark
and he killed with it a machete.
>> We ate shark
until we were sick, actually.
We rolled it into a roast
and spit-fired it
and we cut nice steaks
and we had quite a feed.
Steph, you guys are struggling
just to get by,
and Koror is winning
and then finding shark
and eating big meals.
>> I'm not a good loser.
And for them to win the rewards
and win the immunities
and get lots of food,
it's pretty tough.
>> PROBST: All right.
Let's get to today's
immunity challenge.
First things first.
Katie, I'll take it back again.
Immunity is back up
for grabs.
In tree mail, both tribes
received a miniature version
of a sea star puzzle.
For today's challenge,
both tribes will have identical
life-size sea star puzzles
floating in the ocean.
One person will be your caller.
Two other people will be
responsible
for moving the pieces around.
First tribe to solve the puzzle
wins immunity.
All right, Koror.
Gregg, Caryn and Katie
participated in the reward.
You guys are sitting this out,
along with two other people.
Who are the two
other sit-outs?
>> I'm sitting out.
>> PROBST: Tom and Ian
are also sitting out.
Who's going to be your caller,
Koror?
>> Me.
>> PROBST: Ulong, who's going to
be the caller?
>> Myself.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon.
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Swim on out to the
pontoons, wait for my go.
Here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> The one on the right needs
to go to the empty spot.
That one right there.
The one to the right of you
needs to go to the empty spot.
>> PROBST: Coby definitely has a
plan.
>> Let's go back.
My fault. Let's go back.
>> Go back?
>> Yeah, go back to where it
was.
>> You think if we moved this
over and up, that one over,
that one down, this one over?
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon and Steph
working together,
but not sure on the progress.
Left.
There's a spot.
Yeah!
Finally got that part.
>> PROBST: Top edge.
Koror looks to have a bit
of an edge at this point.
>> Attaboy, Coby.
>> You want to move...
I want that one to be up here.
>> Which one?
>> This one's got to go here.
That one's gotta come over,
that one's gotta go down.
I think if we move
this one back
and start from that side
and bring it up?
>> PROBST: How you doing,
Bobby Jon?
>> I'm trying to get our corners
in order right now.
>> PROBST: Ulong may be worse
off than when you started.
Janu just having a hard time
holding her breath.
>> Behind you, empty spot.
Finally.
We're halfway done, you guys.
>> PROBST: Koror is halfway
there.
>> Good job, Coby.
>> All right.
>> This corner, Steph,
the one you got your hand on,
uh-uh, right here.
>> Right here?
>> Yeah.
Wait a minute,
that is that corner.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, I'm not
sure you've made any progress
since we started.
Steph, want to get up here
for a second?
>> PROBST: Ulong going
to switch out callers.
Switch 'em out and see if we can
get a little more progress.
Steph going to take over
for Ulong.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: Steph surveys.
You in good shape
or bad shape, Steph?
>> We're not in that good
a shape. Um...
>> PROBST: Steph going to have
to make up a lot of ground.
>> That next one, come forward.
This one there needs
to come up here.
>> PROBST: Steph hustling,
trying catch up.
>> Back, empty spot.
>> PROBST: Janu, you look like
you've swam a marathon right
now.
>> That one's got to go
in that corner,
that one's got to go back there.
That piece over there's
got to come here.
That one is going to come.
We're going to go full circle.
Bring that back around.
That one to the left.
>> PROBST: Ulong picking up.
>> Back, empty spot.
>> PROBST: Koror down
to their last few pieces.
They won't be easy.
>> PROBST: Coby very close for
Koror.
He can see it.
>> Come on, Coby!
>> Left empty spot and that's
where we got it.
>> PROBST: Koror one move away
from their sixth straight
immunity.
>> This is it.
This is the last one.
( Koror cheering )
>> PROBST: And with that,
Koror wins immunity
for the sixth straight time.
Koror, once again,
immunity going
back to camp.
Nobody from this tribe
going home.
Ulong, you started making
some progress at the end.
Too little too late.
It's the same old song.
Tribal Council again
and it's going
to be Bobby Jon,
Ibrehem or Steph
who's going home.
Head on back to camp.
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> When we got back to the beach
after the challenge,
we were all shocked
that we couldn't believe we were
going back to Tribal Council.
I think we've...
This has to be a record.
Seven times in a row
for one tribe.
Good God.
I don't want to vote.
>> You got to vote.
>> I just hate it, though,
'cause I think all
of us deserve to be here.
I guess it's always good
to, you know,
expect the worst-case scenario
sometime.
>> Yeah.
Here's the thing.
You're fighting
with these two people
for a million dollars,
but at the same time,
they're still on your team, and
you want your team to do well.
So which one do you pick?
Right now, I'm like a swing
vote.
I got Stephenie who wants me
to go with her
and then I got Ibrehem.
Ibrehem and I have had
pretty much had a little trust
thing since day one.
We're from the same state.
One, two, three.
And we just kind of got
a common theme going
and we know that.
I know that and he knows that.
He's never went and said, "Oh,
you and I have an alliance,"
because I think in some ways
that's kind of stupid,
but in some ways it does matter.
You got it?
>> Way to go, boy.
>> There ain't no fish down
there.
>> You straight?
You getting tired?
>> No, I'm all right.
>> All right.
>> I know Ibrehem would take it
like a man if he wins or loses,
and I know Stephenie would be
a little upset
if I vote, you know, for her
because she thinks
that she and I made this,
you know, big-time agreement.
>> I should have never got
myself in a situation
with two guys from Alabama.
I feel like my fate
is in these two boys' hands.
And it just sucks because
they're the same age,
they're from the same state,
they got a lot in common.
And I'm, like,
the outcast, kind of.
My plan is just get Bobby Jon
alone and talk to him.
I thought we were sticking
together no matter what.
>> Well, we are sticking
together, but it's kind of a
toss-up, you know, between me,
you and him, you know.
I don't deserve to stay
no more than nobody else.
You know?
I mean, really.
>> I think we deserve to stay.
>> I think we do, too.
But, I mean, I ain't
going to count my man out,
which I know what you
and I, you know, discussed.
And I know what he
and I have discussed.
>> So you're not sticking
with your word, then?
>> I've been sticking with
him since day one.
But now I'm sticking
with you, you know.
The way I look it is, we're
going to say okay zip it.
>> I thought...
Yeah, I know, but I thought
that we said if it was us three,
we would vote Ib out.
Yeah, yeah, but I want
to kind of wait
before we start
talking about all that.
I don't really want to talk
about it, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
I'm not going to rule anybody
out until the tribe has spoken.
>> It was a little wishy-washy
his answer.
But I can tell by
the way he's acting,
he's going to vote for me.
I'm just pissed.
It's just wrong.
It's the wrong decision.
It's not my time.
I would love to turn
the tables on him.
Bobby Jon knows how bad
I want to stay,
and I'm not ready to go yet.
And I don't plan on going.
And there's no reason
for me to go.
I mean, I'm thinking about doing
it, 'cause he promised me
and I know he promised you, too.
And why leave it in his hands
when we could end it right now?
>> Yeah.
>> But now he's, like,
undecided, and if we vote for
each other we're going to let
him decide, so I'll vote for
him.
If you want.
>> I'm just being honest, I'll
shoot it to you straight.
I don't know...
I don't know what the hell
I'm going to do.
I hate we're even
in this situation.
>> PROBST ( hoarse voice ):
I want to apologize for my
voice.
I know it's hard to hear.
Bobby Jon...
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: ...who decided that,
that you should be the set of
eyes today, the caller?
>> We all did.
We all did.
And, obviously, it wasn't a
good idea because I think I made
more of a mess than I did
create something that was
supposed to happen,
and it didn't happen.
>> PROBST: You agree with that,
Steph?
Did Bobby Jon screw it up?
>> We just assumed that...
or agreed that
he would be the best, and
he wasn't able to get it,
so we switched out.
I wasn't able really
to get it either, so...
>> PROBST: How frustrating was
it for you today, Steph?
>> It's...
it's so frustrating.
I mean, losing this many times,
>> PROBST: How much do you
scratch your heads at this?
Because it's not like
you're taking on
the same four people.
You've taken on different
combinations of Koror,
and every single time,
they've whupped you.
When you go back to camp and
you're scratching your heads,
what goes through your
head in terms of what is it?
>> We don't...
I mean, we don't come back,
you know, after...
after a challenge,
after we lost, and start
jumping up and down
and giving each other
high-fives on losing.
This isn't fun to come here.
I mean, I...
Jeff, I've been looking at
myself all day thinking, I mean,
I might be the hex,
I might be a curse.
You just don't know
with this tribe.
>> PROBST: So what do you do
tonight?
You guys have to be tight
to some degree.
You're all each other has.
Bobby Jon, are you surprised how
quickly you could become so
close?
>> You know, like, I mean,
I don't drink unless
you know, she went to the well.
I don't get any coconuts
unless he went to the tree
and got them.
I mean, like,
you depend on each other,
and, like, we know which...
what each other is thinking
a lot of times around camp.
I mean, our camp
life is phenomenal.
It's just, we haven't
rose to the occasion.
>> PROBST: So then when it comes
down to writing somebody's name
down tonight, Bobby Jon,
what do you base it on?
>> Man, I tell you, Jeff, I'm
not going to know until the last
second I put that pen down
on that piece of paper.
>> PROBST: So, if it's Steph for
you, why?
Why would you vote
Steph out tonight?
>> For a threat.
That's why I'd vote Steph out,
'cause I think
she can go all the way.
>> PROBST: Ibrehem, if you knew
it was you tonight,
told you right now
you're the one going,
anything you'd want to say
to try and convince
these guys otherwise?
>> I think because I'm a...
I'm a really loyal person,
I think that's one
good thing about me.
If I say I'm going to do
something, I'm going to do it.
I'm not a dishonest person,
for the most part.
>> PROBST: So which is it,
Steph?
Is it... Are you voting tonight
based on loyalty and friendship
or are you voting on
"I want to stay in this game,
and I'm getting rid
of the toughest guy"?
>> I'm actually gonna...
I think I'm going to vote on
what I think would
help me out as a strategy.
>> PROBST: Truth be told,
are you worried tonight
or are you feeling okay?
>> 90% worried.
I mean, it's just, you know,
there's three of us.
Two guys who get along real
well.
I get along with both of them.
I respect both of them.
We all work hard,
but I feel really vulnerable.
And it's, it's sad,
'cause I'm not ready to go.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, worried or
are you in the driver's seat?
>> To me right now
is like me trying to put that
puzzle together today.
It's tough because I think that
I'm just as...
I'm just as vulnerable, too,
Jeff.
I mean, why, why should I stay,
you know?
Why should I stay over them?
It's about to come down to it.
Anything can happen,
anything can.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Steph, you're up.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave the
Tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote,
Ibrehem.
Steph.
One vote Steph,
one vote Ibrehem.
One vote left.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Palau...
Ibrehem.
You need to bring me your
torch.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Ibrehem, the tribe
has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> See you, Ib.
>> PROBST: Well, here's the good
news: In spite of the fact this
tribe of nine has been
decimated, you two still believe
in yourselves as a tribe.
Don't lose that spirit.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Get out of here!
>> PROBST: The rats move in
at Koror.
>> Get out of here.
>> The rats have realized that
we're not a threat to them.
>> Get out of here!
>> PROBST: And Coby's had
enough...
>> These girls don't do
anything.
I want to take all three of
those girls and push them in
that fire.
>> PROBST: ...while Ulong is
down to two.
>> Bobby Jon is turning
into a caveman.
( belches )
>> What can I say?
I totally didn't expect
to be voted off tonight.
So it was a big surprise.
I thought me
and Bobby Jon
had something,
but I guess
I was wrong.
I played the game
the best way I felt
like I knew how
without compromising
my character.
I think I walk away
with just a whole
new respect for life,
not taking things for granted.
It was an experience
I definitely enjoyed.