>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
After their third consecutive
Tribal Council, Ulong was
desperate.
>> I'm gonna stomp anybody's ass
that lags.
>> Tree mail.
>> PROBST: The tribes had a big
decision to make.
>> "Today you must choose one
tribal representative..."
>> I'll speak right out...
>> PROBST: At Koror, Tom spoke
for the tribe and chose Ian as
their representative.
>> Ian, I say you go.
>> PROBST: But the decision
exposed a divide in the tribe.
>> Katie, Jennifer, Gregg, Ian
and Tom are one unit.
So that makes five against four.
We're definitely the underdogs
here.
>> Maybe we'll draw straws or
something.
>> PROBST: At Ulong, the tribe
couldn't make a decision.
You guys don't have a leader,
you can't even pick a
representative.
Give me somebody.
>> James.
>> I wasn't trying to be the
leader, they picked me.
>> PROBST: The tribes competed
in a bathroom build-off.
We're going to judge your
bathroom.
For the winning tribe, our
entire construction department
will build a shelter.
Both tribes squared off.
>> Jenn, is that a boat coming?
>> PROBST: And in the end, it
was Koror that won the new
shelter.
>> Oh, it's a frickin' palace.
It's like the Taj Mahal.
It's fantastic.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Ulong was out for
revenge.
>> We're not going back to
Tribal Council!
>> PROBST: The Ulong women held
their own...
Jenn is in!
Steph wins.
...but the men faltered.
Koror wins their fourth straight
immunity challenge.
Back at Ulong...
>> I have never lost this bad.
>> PROBST: ...the girls were
frustrated and wanted James out.
>> James lost it for all of us.
>> PROBST: But Kim was on the
chopping block as well.
>> She sits on her butt.
She might drink some coconut
juice, you know.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
the women ultimately sided with
the men...
Fourth person voted out
of Survivor: Palau...
...and voted out the weakest
link.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Your shoulder's right on my
head.
(laughing)
(giggling)
>> Don't do that to yourself.
>> In the shelter, people have
teamed off, and Jennifer and
Gregg have definitely teamed
off.
I mean, Jennifer had her hand
on Gregg's stomach, rubbing on
it.
I mean, it's very obvious.
And they won't admit how close
they're getting.
But we can all see it.
They got to think we're stupid
if we can't tell that they're
together.
>> Willard's in the hammock.
>> Willard...!
Where are you?
>> Nice.
>> Can you see the fire?
You're in charge.
Willard...
You're in charge of the fire
unless you wake somebody up.
>> Y'all ready?
>> Hold up, hold up.
>> I don't know that we need the
machete.
>> We don't need it.
>> I've got the bag.
>> You might need it for
something.
(thunder)
>> Everybody in line now.
Let's go.
>> We get back from Tribal
Council, and it's James and
Bobby Jon's idea to go find the
cave because it's going to rain.
>> A tree sticking out.
>> Yeah.
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's really bad.
>> Where the hell are we going?
>> Trying to get to the cave.
>> This is the wrong way.
>> The cave is 300 yards from
the shelter.
I was the one trying to lead us
through there.
And I've never really been real
lost before in the wilderness,
especially at night.
Here's the trail, dude.
>> You on the trail?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> That's not the trail.
>> Y'all, watch out.
>> There's a wall in front of
us, right?
See this here, that's a rock.
>> That's a wall.
>> I think we're totally lost.
>> Come on y'all, this is an
adventure.
>> I just don't want anybody to
get hurt. We're already...
>> Ain't nobody gonna get hurt.
(thunder)
It's gonna be a tree up here.
>> Where are we going?
>> Come on, you have a
better way to get back there?
I can't see. Can you see?
>> No.
>> Well, I'm trying, baby.
But don't get on down my throat,
'cause I don't know what's going
on either.
I'm trying to stay dry,
I'm trying to help out.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Bobby Jon and James were gung
ho about it and I thought it was
insane.
It's the middle of the night,
we can't find that cave.
We're going around in circles
for, like, an hour.
>> Are we supposed to keep
bearing left?
>> I'm going back to camp.
>> Why are you going to go back
to camp by yourself?
>> You can't.
>> Why can't I?
Who says I have to go with you
guys and get lost in the jungle?
I don't want to get
lost in the jungle.
>> Angie wanted to quit.
She's one of those folks
that says, "I can't do this,"
you know, "I'm never going to
find it."
Okay, never say "never."
(thunder)
>> Oh, my God.
>> We don't want to go back to
get wet.
>> I'm just scared to get
struck by lightning.
We're in the middle of a
freakin' jungle.
This is, like, the last place
they say to be.
Let's just go back.
Everybody walk that way, go.
After about an hour in the dark,
we were all tired.
Our feet were killing us.
And we came back to our shelter
and it poured all night.
(thunder)
>> We cannot quit.
We cannot falter.
Y'all want to win, do not quit!
>> Amen.
>> A-Amen.
>> It's gray all the way back.
There's more rain coming.
>> Feel like I slept in a mud
hole.
>> I'm just feeling really
miserable this morning.
No sleep.
We're all freezing.
It's miserable.
Today doesn't look like it's
going to be shaping up too well.
It's pretty dark and stormy
looking.
This is a rough one.
>> It was a tough night.
It was a little grumpy
this morning, you know.
It comes from lack of sleep
and you being the guy up tending
the fire all night.
To make matters worse, I had to
climb over Willard sleeping in
the hammock each time I had to
get up and tend the fire.
We made so many hints to Willard
about, you know, we all
have to help with the fire.
Either he's playing a game
where he's wearing me down
by making me stay up all night,
or he's just got the kind of
attitude where, "Why should I do
it if somebody else is going to
do it for me?"
You know, I mean, because of his
age, he can't contribute a lot.
But he can come out here and put
another log on the fire.
>> He's had plenty of time and
energy to think about what
his role is in this game,
and the longer you keep him
around, the more likely he is to
screw you.
>> Right.
It's discouraging.
>> What an ass.
>> Imagine putting up with that
in the real world?
>> Oh, God.
>> I mean, it's just, like...
You have to bite your tongue
here and just keep playing the
game, and it just infuriates
you.
You just want to unload on the
guy.
You know, tell him where he
belongs.
>> Since we keep winning
immunity, you don't really have
to play, you know, the voting,
the alliance part of the game.
Everyone's sitting pretty,
we keep winning.
Koror keeps getting stronger.
So in a way, because we've been
winning all these immunity
challenges, Willard has been
getting a free ride.
And he's been able
to play this game a lot longer
than he should.
>> PROBST: Welcome, guys.
You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
Here's how it's going to work.
Both tribes are going to race
out to a Japanese shipwreck
to retrieve sake bottles
from the bottom of the ocean.
Using a pulley system,
each tribe will pull
one tribe member out to a buoy.
Directly underneath the buoy
is a shipwreck.
Scattered amongst the shipwreck
are 14 sake bottles.
When you hit the buoy, a tribe
member will dive down,
release the sake bottle, come
back up, get back on the skiff
and their tribe will pull them
back to the start where another
tribe member will get on and do
the same thing.
The first tribe to collect
six sake bottles wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Good news is the
winning tribe will eat tonight.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: Now, for bad the
news.
You'll be dining at Tribal
Council, because win or lose,
both tribes are going to Tribal
Council tonight, both tribes
will vote one tribe member out.
The winning tribe will go
to Tribal Council
and vote somebody out.
They will then cross
to the jury side,
help themselves to some stew
and root beer and listen in
as the losing tribe
has their Tribal Council.
In a game in which knowledge is
power, the winning tribe will
leave Tribal Council with a full
belly and some potentially
vital information to help them
later in the game.
Everybody clear on this?
Koror, you have
four extra members.
You're sitting four people out.
Who is it going to be?
>> Willard, Caryn, Katie and
Janu are sitting out.
>> PROBST: All right, those four
take a spot in the boat,
everybody else, wait for my go.
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
Steph and Jen first on the
skiffs.
Ulong with a bit of a lead.
Steph first to the buoy,
and she's down.
Jen right behind her.
Jen first up, with a bottle for
Koror.
>> Come on, let's go!
>> PROBST: Steph up with a
bottle for Ulong right behind.
Koror back first.
Ulong right behind.
We're dead even.
>> Go, Gregg.
>> Let's go.
>> PROBST: Gregg and Angie
heading out.
Angie first there for Ulong.
Gregg right behind.
Angie up.
Gregg up.
Both heading back.
We're still dead even.
First tribe to six is going to
be eating tonight.
Ulong back first.
Ibrehem on the skiff.
Ulong with a bit of a lead now.
Koror losing time.
Gregg working against them.
There it is.
Gregg's back.
We're tied, two-two, Koror
really falling behind.
Ibrehem down.
Koror really slowing down.
Ibrehem comes up.
>> Got one?
>> PROBST: He doesn't have a
bottle, he's got to go back
down.
Coby going down for Koror.
>> Come on, Ib, come up with
one.
Come on!
>> PROBST: He comes up.
Still doesn't have a bottle.
Coby has one.
He's heading back for Koror.
Koror's made up a lot of time.
They're now in the lead.
>> Come on, Ib!
Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Ibrehem going down
one more time.
>> Got one?
>> Get on the raft!
>> Get on!
>> Get on the raft.
>> Get on the plank!
>> PROBST: Ibrehem does not have
a sake bottle, and he's coming
back.
That is going to hurt Ulong.
Koror back with their third.
Koror leads three-two.
(teams shouting encouragement)
Ibrehem comes back without a
bottle.
One full bottle behind.
>> Way to go, team.
>> PROBST: Tom is down for
Koror.
Tom up with a bottle for Koror.
Bobby Jon down for Ulong.
Bobby Jon is up quickly with a
bottle.
Ulong's going to have to dig
deep.
>> All right, guys!
>> PROBST: Tom back with the
fourth bottle for Koror.
They lead four-two.
>> Beautiful.
>> PROBST: Ian heading into the
water.
Bobby Jon back.
Ulong now at three.
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Ulong's gonna need a
miracle.
Koror leads four-three.
Ian goes down for Koror.
James is in for Ulong.
James is up first.
Ian's having trouble.
>> I can't see any bottles.
>> They're white! They're white!
>> PROBST: This is the break
Ulong needed.
>> They're over to the right!
>> PROBST: James is back.
We're tied at four-four.
Ulong getting back in this.
Steph going down for Ulong.
Ian up with a bottle for Koror.
Steph up very quickly with a
bottle.
She's on the skiff and Ulong is
pulling her back.
Ian back with their fifth
bottle.
Koror leads five-four, and Ian's
going to go right back out.
Everybody's gone now.
Anybody can go from here on out.
Steph heading back out.
We're tied five-five.
Ian holds the key for Koror.
>> Come on, Ian!
>> PROBST: Steph going down for
Ulong.
Ian is up with Koror's sixth
bottle.
All they've got to do is get
him back now.
>> Come on!
Tom!
>> PROBST: Ian coming back with
the winning bottle.
Koror wins reward!
(whooping)
>> All right!
>> PROBST: Frustrated Steph.
Right.
Here's how it's going to work
tonight.
Koror, you will go to Tribal
Council first, where you will
vote somebody out of your tribe.
You will then move to the jury
section and eat stew as you
listen in on Ulong's Tribal
Council where they will vote
another member out of their
tribe.
Get in your outriggers, head
back to camp.
(cheering)
Nice job again, everyone.
(growling like pirates)
>> Today was, was one we had to
win as a team, and we did, and
unfortunately, both tribes have
to vote one member out tonight.
Poor Ulong is really getting
decimated.
I mean, there's gonna be four of
them left and there'll be
eight of us left.
It's just a good thing
Ibrehem didn't do as well as he
should have.
>> Doesn't matter. Even if he
had gotten one, we would still
have been ahead of them.
>> The nice thing is we get to
watch Ulong do it
and see kind of, where the,
where the, uh, the feelings are
and where the strategy is,
and, I mean, tonight a party
in my mouth is gonna be had.
Oh, God, I'm so excited.
I speak Kororese.
>> Kororean.
>> Can I make another
suggestion, too?
Tonight we're going to have
to eat in front of them.
Can we be nice about it and not
giggle and laugh and moan so
much?
>> We're all 21.
♪ I don't have
to go clamming today... ♪
♪ I don't have to go
play in the bay. ♪
(people laughing)
>> Who brought this guy?
Whose friend is he?
♪ Don't have to go
and find seashells.
♪ Poor Ulong is in the Survivor
hell. ♪
>> You're crazy.
>> At the challenge, we had it
in the bag.
Then...
Ibrehem.
We lost because of him.
He gave up.
His heart wasn't in it.
If his heart was in it, he would
have told us, "Look,
I can't do it," you know?
That would have been the manly
thing to do.
>> I can't believe we've lost.
>> Beef stew, you know?
>> I might throw up sitting
there watching them eat it, I
really might.
>> Everything happens for a
reason, though.
You got to think like that.
>> It was such a joke.
>> Yeah. We gotta suffer.
He's his-tor-y.
>> I've been an athlete my
entire life.
I'm just not a good loser.
I just, I don't understand
how this tribe continues to lose
the way it does, and I'm not
good with it, I'm not good with
losing.
I don't know how much more I can
take of it.
I'm just hoping for a merge
really.
I'm going to get water.
>> Who's going for the craft?
I pretty much lost it for the
whole team.
I guess I panicked a little bit
and felt like I was taking too
much time.
And that kind of threw it for
us.
I single-handedly lost that one.
I admit it.
All the other challenges,
I gave my all.
I never quit, but I definitely
think I'm probably the number
one target right now.
If you can, let me know what's
up.
>> I will.
>> You know what I'm saying.
>> Keep me informed.
I know you've got my back.
>> I got it, you know.
It's just, boy, you know,
the cookie crumbles.
You got that?
>> Appreciate it.
>> As much as I do like him
and, and as much as I've grown
to know him, it's fair
to vote Ibrehem tonight.
>> I've said before, the first
time we get to immunity,
I very well may have a problem.
And here we are.
There are situations that can't
be turned around.
It's like trying to fight
gravity or King Canute saying,
"I want the tide to stop."
The tide ain't going to stop
and gravity ain't going
to shut off.
>> What's up, big boy?
>> I just came by. Uh...
I think I'm going tonight.
Do you, can you fit into my
shorts?
>> Oh... Willard.
Don't make me sad.
Probably.
>> You know, it's a game, I had
fun.
I had bad moments,
good moments.
I couldn't play as hard as I
want because of physical
reasons, but it's been okay.
>> Just makes me so mad,
if you go before Katie.
She's so worthless.
But what can we do?
>> It's okay. It's, it's a
game of, of personalities, and I
have almost no ability to
schmooze.
I mean, I just don't have it.
And you end up with my pants,
there's something wrong with
this game.
>> And I get a shirt.
I get a shirt back.
>> Well, that's your shirt.
>> I could absolutely say
with 100% certainty,
tonight will be Willard, and I
don't have the numbers, I can't
change those other peoples'
minds, it's not gonna happen.
All it'll do is set me
apart from the tribe,
and like I said, it's a
popularity contest.
If I act like a bitch,
nobody's gonna like me.
I'm not going to stick around.
>> Everybody's favorite
curmudgeon.
>> "Curmudgeon," that's a good
word.
>> Yes, it is.
>> The only person pissing me
off is Katie, but nobody'll do
anything about it.
She doesn't do anything, and
she's still here.
I don't even care how far I get
in the game, but if Katie
gets further than me, I will
just puke, puke, puke.
You want to walk?
>> Yeah, I'm cool.
Which way? That way?
>> Sure. Don't...
don't tell anybody this.
>> I won't.
>> Because I trust you, and
we've built a relationship.
And I think what's good about
this is it's an equal benefit
for both you and me.
>> I agree.
>> Right now, there's, like, a
soft alliance between me, Tom...
>> Ian, Katie...
>> Um... Ian, Katie and Jenn.
>> Right.
>> And Tom and Ian are really
just strong, and that bond is
just too tight, you know?
Jenn and I feel like we're on
the outside of that alliance.
>> Right.
>> And we feel, like, once
Willard and Caryn are gone,
if it comes to seven people,
then we switch--
me, Jenn, you and Janu.
And then we start picking them
off.
>> The main interesting thing
that happened today...
was with Ken and Barbie.
Gregg basically told me,
secretly-- and not to tell
anybody, and I won't-- that him
and Jennifer want to make a
secret alliance to the top four
with me and Janu.
And they want to pick everybody
else off, including Tom and Ian.
>> Tom especially?
>> Tom especially.
>> Tom's my biggest
bull's-eye right now.
I want Tom off.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> What?
Out of the blue!
>> I... I'm in a good situation
because I can be part
of that five-person alliance
and get information from
them and control them.
>> The game is now just now
getting interesting
now that we're having to vote
people off.
I'm very excited.
I love that the game is going to
a new level.
I can't wait.
>> So we're good?
Everything's cool, right?
>> Yep. We got the plan.
>> Right.
>> And I think, you know...
>> Willard seems to have a good
attitude about it, too.
>> Right.
Nobody wants to go home,
but you got to do it
with a stiff upper lip also,
as most of us will at one time
or another.
>> So Jenn and I are in the
middle to navigate which way
we really want to go,
and that's a luxury.
If we wanted to, we could flip
from the Katie, Tom and Ian
side to the Janu and Coby side.
And we could start picking off
who I perceive to be the bigger
strengths in Tom and Ian.
Jenn and I--
people look at us as, oh, we're
just, like, a cute couple.
Well, I think we're thinking
a hell of a lot more than them.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
and approach the flame.
Dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual
of Tribal Council.
As long as you have fire, you're
still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
That will be the case for one of
you tonight.
So we have a lot to cover.
Let's talk about relationships,
leadership, friendship.
Katie, who's leading this tribe
right now?
>> Depends how you want to
define "leader."
At challenges, Tom definitely
is a leader.
If you're looking at leader as
someone that provides food,
that's Ian.
>> PROBST: Tom, did you come in
here to be the leader?
>> My intention was to come in
here, be the 40-year-old dad,
fade into the background.
I ended up in a tribe
initially physically
weaker than the other tribe.
And every one of us had
to turn it on 110% to win those
immunities.
And we see the results.
>> PROBST: Coby, are you
social with this tribe?
>> I'm very social...
which could bite me in the end.
I get along with everybody.
You know, when you're too
friendly, and you're too busy
of a bee, people watch you too
much, I guess.
>> PROBST: So what do you do
to... to counter that?
>> I don't care.
I'm just being me.
I am social.
I am a butterfly.
I do want to talk to everybody.
So I just do it, and if that
costs me the game
in the end, well, so be it.
>> PROBST: Gregg, what
friendships have you seen
develop?
Are you starting to notice
just a natural
bonding between people?
>> You definitely see that.
Tom and Ian spend a lot of time
together.
You know, it's like a father-son
relationship.
>> I'm the father.
>> But, at the same time, we all
appreciate that, you know?
It's not something that's hidden
or secretive.
Coby and Janu have been getting
along great.
And Willard and Caryn have
been getting along great.
Katie's been spreading the
wealth.
She's been, you know, loving
everyone, and everyone's
enjoying her company.
>> Thanks.
>> Where does that leave Jenn
and Gregg?
>> So, you know, that leaves me
and Jenn alone.
>> PROBST: So that's a different
type of friendship then?
>> We have a strong bond, just
as everyone else here, and it's
nothing you know, super
intense at this point.
>> PROBST: Willard, how do you
think you are perceived?
Probably as one of the weaker
players on the team.
I'm not as strong as I thought
I'd be.
And I think people
understand that.
Not a good position to be in.
>> PROBST: Gregg, at this point,
how big an issue does trust
become?
>> It's about to kick in.
It's about to really kick in.
This is our first time here,
and now we're faced with the
reality of voting people off,
and so the trust that we think
that we have or hope that we
have is going to be tested
because it hasn't been tested
yet.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Willard, you're up.
>> You're crabby and you're
bitter.
Bye.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final--
person voted out
will be asked to leave the
Tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Katie.
Willard-- one vote Katie,
one vote Willard.
Willard-- two votes Willard,
one vote Katie.
Willard-- that's three votes
Willard.
Willard-- four votes Willard.
One vote Katie.
Fifth person voted
out of Survivor: Palau,
Willard.
That's five, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Willard, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Stay strong, stick to the
plan, finish them off.
(several saying farewells)
>> PROBST: Okay, Koror, you are
now a tribe of eight.
Willard voted out.
Your work here is done
for your voting.
We'll now bring in the Ulong
tribe.
You can then partake
in your reward.
Grab your torches.
Cross over to the jury side.
>> I surprised myself out here
by not being quite as strong
as I expected to be.
There are times I get crabby,
and I know that can bother
people.
But there has been many years
since I've been in a situation
where I'm deprived of water and
sleep.
I think the tribe as a whole
are good people by and large.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the Ulong tribe...
who I'm sure is going
to enjoy this.
Koror, go ahead and pull off the
cover.
(all expressing awe)
Biscuits! (singing)
>> PROBST: Stew, bread, and root
beer.
(all expressing awe)
>> Oh, it smells so delicious.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Pass it out.
>> It smells so good.
>> Let's all wait to eat.
Get excited, Tom.
>> Oh, I am, I am.
>> Don't be bashful.
Don't be bashful; I'm a skinny
man.
>> We get two a piece, it looks
like.
(Ian chuckles)
>> Oh, my God.
>> Yes!
I think I'm going to cry.
Are you all going to cry?
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: Just so we're all
clear, part of Koror's reward
was to be here for Tribal
Council tonight to listen in,
potentially gather information
that will help them later
in the game.
They're not going
to be asking questions,
just listening...
and eating.
First question I have is,
it seems as though you brought
your entire camp.
You brought shovels,
you brought your Home Depot kit.
Why is that, Bobby Jon?
>> I mean, we don't ever know
what's going to happen next.
We don't know if we're gonna
merge.
We decided we'd bring
everything, and if we have to
take it back, then we'll take it
back, but... I'm sure we've got
to take it back.
>> PROBST: Yeah, we're not
merging.
Angie, are you hiding your face
because you can't stand
to look at the food?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You're genuinely
upset.
Is it frustration?
Are you sad?
Are you...?
>> I'm frustrated.
I'm so frustrated.
I mean, it was
really close today.
We really... we needed this.
And it's not just like today
was a loss of food.
It was a loss of, like, you
know...
winning today would have been
a real big boost to team morale.
It's not all about the food.
It's just that after
consistently losing,
it would have been nice to win,
and win something we all wanted.
>> PROBST: Stef, how is it for
you?
>> It makes me sick.
It makes me sick to know
that we would have been
eating a nice meal.
We almost had it in
the palm of our hands
except for one mistake.
We had a great lead
and blew it all away.
It's hard.
I can't even look over there.
I don't even know
who got voted out.
>> PROBST: James, you guys have
hung in there.
You've tried to keep a good
attitude.
Today looked like it put a knife
in the back of this tribe.
>> We wanted it, man.
Our desire was there.
We was pulling as hard as we
could.
As fast as we could just to get
this one reward.
We all wanted it.
Ever since we've been starving.
It was disappointing.
>> PROBST: Ibrehem?
>> You know, everyone's really
emotional right now.
All they're thinking about
is what's the last challenge.
I mean, I can go back to other
challenges where other people
haven't done as well, but that's
just not the way I do business.
I guess I wish people would kind
of look collectively at how
I've done in challenges.
Then put it together
rather than just put your fate
at one challenge, and if you've
made one mistake, too bad.
I mean, it seems like
all I've heard today is,
wow, we could have really been
eating that beef stew right now,
like that's the end of the game,
like beef stew is it.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
But before you vote, Ulong,
Koror, you are going to vote.
Last part of your reward is,
you're going to vote to give
immunity to one person from
Ulong.
This is an individual
decision.
And you are voting for
the person you want to be safe
tonight at the vote.
Whoever has the most votes
will get immunity on Ulong.
Then Ulong will vote.
Janu, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
To be clear, these votes
are for immunity.
Very rare in this game
you want to see your name.
Tonight is one of those times.
Person who has the most votes
will be immune from Tribal
Council.
Angie.
One vote Angie.
Ibrehem.
One vote Angie, one vote
Steph.
One vote Angie, one vote Steph,
one vote Ibrehem.
Bobby Jon.
That's one vote each
for Angie, Stef, Ibrehem
and Bobby Jon.
Two immunity votes
for Stephenie.
That's two votes
for Bobby Jon.
Ibrehem has one, Angie has one.
Ibrehem now has two.
One vote left.
Here's where we stand.
Stef has two,
Bobby Jon has two,
Ibrehem has two.
Angie has one.
Immunity goes to...
Ibrehem.
>> PROBST: Koror, your work is
done.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Now it is time for you to vote.
Ibrehem is safe.
Everybody else is fair game.
James, you're up.
Angie, sorry.
It's not your time to go.
Sorry.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Angie.
Bobby Jon.
One vote Angie, one vote Bobby
Jon.
James.
One vote Angie, one vote
Bobby Jon, one vote James.
That's two votes Bobby Jon.
One vote Angie, one vote James.
I'll read the last vote.
Angie.
We have a tie.
That's two votes Bobby Jon,
two votes Angie.
Here's what's going to happen,
Angie and Bobby Jon, because
you're tied, you will not vote.
We will vote again with James,
Ibrehem and Stef.
After this round of voting,
there will be no tie.
To be clear, you're voting for
Bobby Jon or Angie.
James, you're up.
>> PROBST: I'll read the votes.
First vote, Angie.
I'll read the second vote.
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor: Palau,
Angie.
There are three votes.
It only takes two.
Angie, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Steph, rock on for the
ladies.
>> PROBST: Well, you've had a
rough first 12 days.
And even though you are down
to four tribe members,
the fact remains,
you are still a tribe
and the good news is
you still seem to believe it.
Grab your torches,
head back the camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
>> You cost us the game
because...
>> PROBST: Ibrehem faces the
music.
>> You went down three times,
didn't come up with a bottle.
>> PROBST: A massive storm
hammers Koror.
>> You a little worried?
This isn't going to go anywhere.
There's no way.
>> PROBST: And Janu pays the
price.
>> It's so hard.
>> I'm very proud of my
accomplishments out here.
I mean, I did a lot better than
I ever thought that I would.
And I'm happy I came out here
and did something
I've never done before.
It was a different and
refreshing experience,
you know, and definitely more
appreciation for the things
that I take for granted.
All those little things in life,
never going to take that
for granted ever again.