>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
In the island nation of Palau,
20 new castaways began their
adventure with a big twist.
There are two immunity
necklaces-- one for the first
woman, one for the first man--
who can get to shore and claim
them.
Go!
With no other information
to guide them, the race was on.
Ian and Jolanda were the first
to claim the necklaces.
>> Whoo! Good job!
>> We're not a tribe.
We don't have our buffs.
We don't have a clue what's
happening next.
>> All right, see if we
can get this going.
>> PROBST: With all 20 on one
beach, and no fire to boil
water, things got even worse
on day two...
All right, Ian, take
a spot right over here,
Jolanda right over here.
...when the survivors finally
learned the value
of the immunity necklaces.
We're going to divide
into two tribes
with nine members each.
There are 20 of you.
Two people will be sent home.
(survivors groaning)
Ian and Jolanda made the first
of the schoolyard picks.
>> Katie.
>> Bobby Jon.
>> PROBST: And the two tribes
were chosen, one by one.
>> Willard.
>> PROBST: Willard was the last
member picked for the older
Koror Tribe.
>> Angie.
>> PROBST: And Angie was the
last picked for the younger
Ulong Tribe.
Jonathan and Wanda were out.
(cheering)
>> Go get 'em, Wanda!
>> I was really, really,
really sad.
I'm going to wipe my tears.
That's in the past.
It's a whole new game.
>> PROBST: All right.
Let's hand out the buffs.
Koror, you will wear brown.
You guys are Ulong.
You'll wear blue.
Survivors ready.
Go!
At the challenge, the tribes
competed for immunity
and whatever survival items
they chose to take.
The older Koror tribe took
only the flint to make fire...
>> Come on! We got to go!
>> PROBST: ...while Ulong
struggled with more supplies.
Koror is up and over.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Koror's decision to
travel light secured them
victory...
Koror wins immunity and reward!
...and earned them the right
to choose a campsite.
You can either go back
to what you know
or you can start fresh.
>> New adventure.
>> PROBST: You're going to
take your chances.
>> We're going to take our
chances.
>> PROBST: But on the way
to their new beach, disaster
struck the winning Koror tribe.
>> Oh, my God!
>> All of the supplies to make
fire went straight down.
It was just like, "Did this
really happen?"
>> We're in a worse scenario
than we originally had.
>> PROBST: Back at Ulong,
Angie knew she was a target
going into Tribal Council.
>> You don't think I remember
exactly the order in which
we got picked for tribes?
The only reason we lost the
challenge is 'cause we didn't
leave soon enough.
>> PROBST: But Stephenie felt
Jolanda had held them back
at the challenge.
>> We made a dumb mistake,
and it's because of one person,
I feel.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Angie received three votes...
First person voted out
of Survivor: Palau...
...but it was Jolanda
who was voted out.
Jolanda, the tribe has spoken.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Another day in paradise.
>> Today we won immunity,
which was fabulous.
We won a great reward
which was the flint,
and up until that point,
everything was just wonderful.
And of course, then there was
a turn of events with the
capsizing of the boat, and...
the flint is at the
bottom of the ocean,
so we can't even get fire.
>> It's a bummer and a buzz
kill, but like we said,
it was just like a car accident,
and we just got
to get back from it.
Get around the shock of it.
(squeaking)
(Janu shrieks)
(shrieking)
>> Oh, my God, there were three!
>> There's a lot of them...
>> When I first saw the rats,
oh, my God, saw three of them,
and they were just
(trills tongue) going to town.
(gasps)
I hear them.
Like, they're right behind
there.
(squeaking)
(gasps)
What?
>> You know what?
I saw something, but...
>> They're, like, walking
around.
They're not afraid of anything.
See? They're right there.
>> Ooh!
>> Ew!
>> Get out!
>> They're right there.
>> I know it's mind
over matter, and I know
if you don't mind,
it doesn't matter,
but, ooh, I mind and it matters.
I just can't stand those things.
They're huge.
Ugh!
>> Tom, I love the, uh,
the new campsite choice.
>> Really?
>> Although, do you think
there could be a worse island
than this?
>> Oh, I'm sure there are.
>> You think so?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> It wasn't safe for us
to choose this island.
It was just a quick decision
we made, and I-I regret that
we didn't think it through.
Tom, having taken the leader
role in the tribe,
said, "Let's go for it.
It's an adventure."
It was a rash choice made in a
moment that could really affect
the game for this tribe.
The way the whole thing came
down, I think Willard said, "I
think we should take a vote."
And you said, "I think
we should do it..."
>> Oh... okay.
>> "We-We're on for another
adventure, it's part of...
we're here for an adventure."
Without having...
>> I-I just... I'm gonna
disagree just because...
I-I thought we should go
back, too, and then...
>> You did?
>> ...three guys-- three
people-- were all saying,
"No, let's go to a new place.
We're out of coconuts."
>> Can we agree that
we should have a vote?
>> Definitely.
>> Even if it... if it's just
to make a decision.
Okay, okay, guys.
Raise your hand.
Who wants to go? Stay?
Raise if you want to go.
>> Caryn's really annoying,
because she has not stopped
talking about how this island
sucks and how everyone didn't
want to come here.
(thunder crashing)
>> Oh, no!
>> We only had a second to
decide, and the majority was,
like, "Let's go," you know?
New tribe, new camp.
Unfortunately,
it was the wrong decision.
Oh, well, we're here.
Get over it.
(thunder crashing)
>> We went to our first
Tribal Council,
and we got rid of Jo.
I think it was a great decision,
actually.
I think our whole team thinks
it, our whole tribe thinks it
was.
>> It's time to get up, y'all.
>> Mmm...
>> Without Jolanda around,
everybody's feeling good, you
know, 'cause there's nobody
telling people what to do.
We're not going
to follow a leader.
>> So what should we do?
>> Well...
>> Wake up first.
>> Yeah.
>> We can make our own decisions
and be democratic about it.
We're Americans, and we're going
to do democracy.
Come on, y'all.
Gather around.
>> See what we got.
>> You ready?
>> Yeah.
Get your ass up here, Ibrehem.
>> All right.
>> I hear you.
>> Maybe not.
(chuckles)
>> Go ahead, Bobby.
>> "Keep on your toes
while making this run.
"Your rivals will seek
to spoil your fun.
"You'll, too, have the chance
to spoil their mood.
Stay out of the water,
and you may catch more food."
>> I think we might fight
people.
>> Yeah, we're gonna... yeah.
>> I'm not quite sure
of my game plan yet.
I know that obviously there are
people who did vote for me,
and so, uh, I just want
to make myself
a valuable asset to this tribe.
If I don't, I'll probably
be on the chopping block again.
>> PROBST: Come on in.
Take a spot on the mat.
We'll now bring in Ulong.
Jolanda voted out at the first
Tribal Council.
Koror, how's the fire
working out?
>> It's not too good.
We capsized yesterday.
>> We just kind of lost it.
>> PROBST: You lost your fire?
That made Jeff really happy.
>> As well it should.
>> We're going to find it.
We're the Bad News Bears, man.
Our back's against the wall,
and we're coming on strong.
>> PROBST: You guys ready
for today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: It is for reward.
Here's how it works.
You will attempt to cross
a balance obstacle course.
Moving one tribe member at a
time, you'll begin by swinging
over a trench.
You'll then make your way
over three rolling drums,
across a balance beam
and over a wobbly bridge.
Finally, you're going to cross
a rope bridge where' you'll
retrieve a flag and make your
way back to the start.
Along the way, members
of the other tribe are going to
try to knock you off by
swinging heavy bags of sand.
First tribe to collect
ten flags wins reward.
If at any time you're knocked
off the course or you fall off
the course, go back to the
start.
Each tribe will assign
two members to be in charge
of swinging the heavy bags.
Only rule: everyone has to cross
the rope swing at least once.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: If you can't get food
with this, you don't deserve
to be out here.
>> Oh, hell, yeah!
Come on, man.
>> PROBST: Mask and snorkel,
fins...
>> Oh... Yes.
>> PROBST: ...spear.
>> I love you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: In addition, Ulong,
since you haven't won it yet,
you're playing for flint.
>> You the man.
>> PROBST: Koror, who are going
to be the two people responsible
for swinging the bags?
>> Myself and Gregg.
>> PROBST: Tom and Gregg.
Ulong?
Jeff and Ibrehem.
Okay, Koror, you have
one extra member.
You're sitting somebody out.
You cannot sit out the same
person in back-to-back
challenges.
Who's sitting out?
>> Willard.
>> PROBST: Willard's going
to sit this one out.
Take your spots.
Wait for my "go."
Here we go for reward.
Survivors ready.
Go!
James and Coby both across.
James making quick work.
>> Come on, baby!
>> Whoo!
>> James!
>> Go, Coby.
>> You got it, baby.
>> Come on, James.
>> PROBST: James has a flag.
He's heading back.
>> Come on, James.
>> PROBST: Coby's in.
Ian on the course.
Oh, no!
He doesn't make it.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon's on the
course.
>> Relax, relax, relax.
>> Get that thing off me!
>> There you go...
>> PROBST: He's still on!
Ian has a flag.
>> Yeah, you got it, Ian.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon has a flag,
he's heading back.
Ian trying to make up
some ground.
>> Oh, you're in!
>> PROBST: Oh! Ian's in.
Oh!
He's hanging on the barrels,
he's hanging on.
He's still on, still on.
(groans)
And he's out.
>> Go. You can do it.
>> PROBST: Katie having trouble.
Katie has to get across
before Koror can continue.
Angie is across.
>> Way to go, Angie!
>> Whoo!
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Angie's got a flag,
heading back.
>> Get down low.
Crawl!
Good job, Angie.
>> PROBST: Angie making
a run for it.
>> Whoo!
>> Yeah!
>> Way to go, Angie.
>> PROBST: There she goes.
Angie puts Ulong on the board
with their first flag.
Ashlee's across.
Katie still struggling.
>> Whoo!
>> You can do it.
That's okay.
>> PROBST: Ashlee has a flag.
She's going to start
heading back.
>> Go, girl. Come on.
>> You got it. You got it.
>> Ashlee almost there.
>> Swing! Good, good. Yes!
>> PROBST: Ulong up 2-0.
Stephenie's across for Ulong.
>> Good job, Steph.
>> Katie, keep your knees up.
You're dropping them too soon.
>> PROBST: Stephenie has a flag.
She's going to start heading
back.
Katie's across!
She's on the course!
>> Let's go, girl.
>> PROBST: Steph is across!
Ulong leads 3-zip,
but Koror is now back in this.
Kim is on the course for Ulong.
>> You go, girl.
>> That's it, Katie.
>> Come on, Katie.
(shouting)
>> PROBST: Kim passes Katie.
>> Come on, Kim.
>> PROBST: Kim coming back.
>> Good job, Kim.
>> Come on, Kim, you got it.
>> PROBST: Whoa, just misses
her.
Katie spent a lot of time
on the course.
>> Katie, if you're too tired,
just bail.
>> PROBST: Kim's there.
Ulong in the lead, 4-zip.
Angie back on the course.
Too tired to continue.
Katie just bails.
Janu on the course
for the first time.
>> Get your knees up.
>> PROBST: Angie's unstoppable,
back with another flag.
>> Angie, you frickin' rock.
>> PROBST: Ashlee's across!
Janu has a flag,
and she's heading back.
>> Let's go, Janu!
You're doing fine!
>> PROBST: Ashlee has a flag.
She's going to start
heading back.
>> Yeah, Janu!
>> PROBST: Janu across
with the first score for Koror.
Ashlee's across.
Ulong leads 6-1.
Jenn's across and on the course.
>> That's it, Jenn.
>> All right, Jenn.
>> PROBST: James is on the
course.
>> Lean your head down!
You got it. Yes!
>> PROBST: Jenn and James
on the rope bridge.
>> You got it, James.
>> Good job, James.
>> PROBST: James has a flag.
He's heading back.
Jenn has a flag.
She's heading back.
>> Come on, James.
>> PROBST: James easily deflects
that.
>> Jenn, you're looking great.
Let's go. Nice.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Ulong leads 7-1.
Bobby Jon's on the course.
>> That's right.
>> PROBST: Jenn's across.
>> Come on, Jenn.
>> Let's go, Bobby Jon.
>> PROBST: Koror now with two.
A lot of ground
to make up for Koror.
And just like that, Caryn takes
a hard one on the hip.
Ian on the course.
Ian... off the course.
Bobby Jon has a flag.
He's heading back.
>> Mind over matter.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: Coby getting
centered.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: And it...
doesn't help.
Coby's out.
>> Come on, Bobby.
>> Let's go, let's go.
>> PROBST: Janu not giving up.
>> You got it, Janu!
>> PROBST: Give her some room,
B.J.
Share that pontoon.
(yelling)
>> Take your time.
Take your time.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon is across.
(yelling)
And he beats himself up
as a reward.
Ulong with eight flags.
Janu worn out.
Stephenie back on the course.
Stephenie... Whoa, whoa!
>> Good job.
>> Beat her there,
beat her there, Janu.
>> PROBST: Janu and Steph
on the rope bridge.
Janu has another flag.
Steph has a flag.
Janu working the barrels.
>> Come on, Janu,
you're almost there now.
>> You got it, Janu.
>> You got it, Steph.
Come on!
>> Go, Steph!
>> PROBST: Janu across with
a flag for Koror.
Stephenie's across
with flag number nine.
9-3. Ulong leads.
Ulong needs only one more flag.
Kim could be the winner.
At stake: fishing gear and fire
for Ulong.
Ian has another flag.
Kim has a flag.
Both heading back.
>> Stay low, Kim.
>> PROBST: Tom, ooh, just
misses.
>> You got it, Kim.
>> Good job, Kim.
>> PROBST: Koror with four
if he can hang on,
and he doesn't.
(cheering)
Kim is this close to victory
for Ulong, and she's across.
(cheering)
Ulong wins reward!
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Ulong, nice job.
Here's fire.
Who wants it?
(whooping)
>> PROBST: You now have fishing
gear and fire.
It should completely
change life at your camp.
Koror, I know what you're doing
this afternoon.
You're looking for that flint.
Head back to camp.
(all whooping)
>> Oh, my God.
That was so awesome.
>> We need to go catch us
some fish.
>> Hell, yeah.
>> I want to get some water.
>> 16 fish would be good
for us tonight.
>> After winning the flint
and the sling and the snorkel
and mask and fins,
now we can eat.
Now we can actually have
some protein.
>> Angie!
>> I'm tougher...
>> Motivated us all, girl.
>> When people think...
I know I am.
Everybody was like, "Wow, you
did so great, you did so great."
And I was like, "Oh, my God,
I needed this so badly."
This is exactly what I needed.
I was like, I was ready to cry
'cause I was just so relieved.
>> She... she showed
me something.
>> I definitely judged Angie
way too quickly.
She went into a challenge
and dominated.
I mean, completely dominated.
I don't know what got into her,
but it was good
and it totally changed
the whole morale
of our whole tribe.
(murmuring)
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Yeah!
>> Oh, my God.
We're gonna drink water.
Oh, my God.
>> I love fire.
It makes me want to cry.
>> The second we got fire
started, I wanted to try and see
if we could catch some fish.
Maybe even go explore and see
what's all around us.
(laughing)
>> There's got to
be bigger fish somewhere.
>> I saw some big ones
in there, dude.
>> Well, at least we know
that if there are some
big fish, we can get them.
You know, I didn't get a whole
lot, but I got enough
so that everybody could have a
couple of pinches of protein.
>> Are you serious, bro?
>> That's what I'm talking
about, Jeff, bring in the bacon.
>> Being well-fed and
well-nourished is the huge
advantage at the next immunity
challenge.
I'm happy that they don't have
their flint, and I hope
they don't find it.
>> We're getting our flint
and steel.
We dropped the box,
and we gotta go find it today.
>> We went out at the absolute
worst time,
and the current was ripping
like I've never seen
the ocean tide rip.
It was like, almost like being
in a fast-moving river.
We were paddling as fast
as we could and just barely
holding position.
Come on, Ian!
>> Give him the anchor. Go!
On your right.
>> You've got to keep paddling.
>> I don't know if
we were that far over.
>> I don't think
it was that far over.
>> But I do think
it was slightly that way.
They're going to be so
disappointed when they come
back, if they don't get it.
>> Okay, I see it, I see it,
I see it.
(screams excitedly)
Don't lose the spot.
We're drifting.
It was definitely
the strongest current
I've ever faced in my life.
And the box
was about 25 feet down.
We tried everything;
we tried hooking the anchor
into the handle on the box
and bring it up, that up,
but it kept slipping.
>> Got it?
(Ian grunts)
>> I feel like I lost it.
>> Do you see it?
>> As I got more and more tired,
it became more and more
difficult to get to the bottom,
became more and more difficult
to tread water.
So, there were a couple of times
when I was like, "Okay,
"you know, I'm underwater;
I don't know if I'm going to be
able to make it."
I had it hooked again.
You see it?
>> That it right there?
>> I saw it when I just
scratched the box.
>> I got it!
Hey, guys, just bring it over
quick, please.
Hurry.
Yeah!
(screams excitedly)
(yells and laughs)
>> Ah-ha-ha!
>> Yeah!
>> Yay!
(cheering)
(screaming jubilantly)
>> Getting the box
and having it was like,
I mean, it was like
running the marathon
and winning first place.
Once we got it into the boat,
it was like, man, it was like
holding on to a big piece
of gold.
(laughing)
(whooping)
>> Nice job, Gregg.
(laughing)
(laughing elatedly)
>> It's one of the happiest
moments of my life.
It was definitely a high
for all of us.
And even though
we lost the challenge,
it really felt like
we won the day.
>> Come on, fire.
>> Okay, okay, blow.
Don't blow too hard.
>> Oh, my God.
(indistinct voices)
(clapping)
>> Good job, guys.
>> A group effort, right there.
>> Isn't that beautiful?
>> I'm so proud of you guys.
>> A good day. A good day.
We can be proud.
>> We got a lot of clam.
>> Look at all of them.
>> You want just to cook it all?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You know, I hate clams, but
I know this is going to be good.
>> Yeah. I haven't had
giant clam before.
>> Well, first time for
everything, right?
>> Tonight is gonna be
our first time we had fire,
our first time we have water
and our first time we're eating
in four days
since we've been here.
We're all famished
and we're ready to chow down.
>> Oh, my God, it's so good.
How's the seaweed?
>> Oh, my God.
You know what?
We can't complain
right now, for real.
>> Oh, I know.
>> Hell, no.
>> We haven't eaten in four
days.
>> We, for the first night,
had actual food besides
coconuts.
Ashlee didn't want any of it.
>> You don't like clam?
>> The way we're gonna
advance ourselves
is be a strong team
all the way through,
and if we have someone
slowing us down,
I hope that that doesn't
bring down our team.
>> Ashlee went into the shelter,
and she went to sleep.
This fire was a big, big thing,
and she should have
came outside and just
kind of sat there.
Sometimes we do things
we don't want to do,
but it's just things you need
to do, 'cause we are a tribe
here and, you know, people will
get voted off this tribe
in this game we're playing.
>> I'm passing out.
>> I'm fighting to stay
awake right now.
>> Yeah, I-I think I'm gonna...
I'm gonna crash.
>> Kim's been snuggling on Jeff
a lot, and I'm not
quite sure how that...
if she's playing him or not.
I mean, two-people alliance
is a very strong alliance,
and so I'm not sure
if they're kind of
buddying up to make an alliance.
And so I'm kind of waiting to
see how that all will play out.
>> Oh, look.
>> What do you think it is?
>> Dishes. Military dishes.
It's a code.
Lear... Learn.
>> T...
>> "Learn this."
It's "Learn this."
We need to learn this code.
Hey, guys!
>> Guys, we got tree mail.
>> It's Morse Code.
>> The tree mail just came
and we're about to all
learn Morse Code.
Right now, we've all
broken it off into sections,
'cause there's eight people.
We don't know if that's
a good strategy or not,
but we think it's
the best one we got.
Does anybody want to quiz me?
>> All right, W?
>> Dot-dash-dash.
>> Winning the other day
definitely gave us
a confidence boost,
but we're going to have
an immunity challenge here,
and we got to win that, too.
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first.
Give it up, Caryn.
Immunity back up for grabs.
Ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yep.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: You received
tree mail this morning.
It said learn Morse Code.
I hope you did.
On my "go," you'll swim out
to a floating platform.
You'll dive down ten feet,
where you'll find a rope
that's strung through a barrel
and attached to a footlocker
that is 50 feet away.
While underwater,
you're gonna pull on a rope,
and as you do you'll bring that
footlocker closer and closer.
Every ten feet, a marker buoy
will pop up showing you
how far you have to go.
Once you've released all five
buoys, that footlocker will be
right in front of you.
You can open it.
Eight mess kits will pop up.
Bring them back with you to
shore, you'll then use the Morse
Code painted on the mess kits
to decode a hidden word.
First tribe to solve
the puzzle wins immunity.
Safe from the vote.
For the losers, a trip
to Tribal Council, you will vote
one member out of your tribe.
Make sense?
Koror, you have one extra
member-- got to sit somebody
out; you cannot sit out the same
person.
Willard sat out in the last
challenge.
Katie. All right.
Everybody else take your spots.
Wait for my "go."
Here we go. For immunity.
Survivors ready.
Go!
All eight have to get to the
pontoon before you can dive
down.
Got to have everybody
at the pontoon before you
can start pulling on the rope.
Willard falling behind.
(indistinct talking)
Ulong, go down.
>> Go. Go.
>> PROBST: Koror has to wait.
They cannot begin until
Willard gets to the pontoon.
Ulong getting a big head start.
Steph heading down.
>> Let's go.
Come on, Willard.
Let's get him, pull him up.
>> PROBST: Go, Koror.
Coby, Tom going down together.
Both tribes underwater.
Ulong making progress.
They're only 40 feet away now.
Tom made up a lot of ground
on that.
Angie's heading down.
Ian and Tom, going down
together.
Koror has a buddy system.
>> PROBST: Koror with the lead.
>> Got 'em on the run.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: Ashlee going down
for Ulong.
>> Aah!
>> You guys ready to go?
Ready to go next?
>> PROBST: Kim, hanging on.
Tom heading down for Koror.
Koror pulling ahead.
Jeff taking a good long rest;
he heads back down.
Jeff not down very long.
Ibrehem also right back up.
Koror, getting that footlocker
closer and closer.
Only ten feet to go.
>> Guys, we're way ahead.
>> PROBST: Ulong falling behind.
>> We gotta keep going.
We gotta keep going.
>> PROBST: Kim, the only one who
has not been down for Ulong.
Steph heading back down.
Ulong with a lot of ground
to still make up.
Ian heading down for Koror.
Koror's got their trunk.
Got to open your trunk
and release the mess kits.
Ian releases the locker.
It's open.
Koror has to unclip
eight mess kits.
>> I got two here.
>> PROBST: Let's go, Ulong.
Immunity at stake.
Ulong still struggling to get
their footlocker to them.
We got 'em all.
Go!
Koror has all eight mess kits.
They're heading into shore
to solve the puzzle.
>> All right, guys, you got
this!
>> PROBST: You're good.
Take off the burlap.
>> "Immunity."
Did you see...?
>> PROBST: Let's go, Ulong!
>> Come on!
>> I...
>> Y...
>> T...
>> Use the other "I."
>> No, "M" is...
"M" is dash, dash...
>> Dash, dash...
>> M...
>> Willard...
>> That's not...
>> Yes.
>> Check it.
>> You sure?
>> PROBST: Koror...
(cheering)
wins immunity!
(cheering continues)
Koror, congratulations.
Nobody going home
from your tribe.
Ulong, good effort.
Sorry to say, another visit
to Tribal Council.
Another tribe member going home.
Up to you to figure out
who that's gonna be.
Head on back to camp.
>> When we lost the challenge
today, everybody was so
disappointed, and to make
matters worse, it was raining,
so our main priority was,
oh, crap, I hope our fire
didn't burn out.
>> Get this.
>> Luckily, we were able to
scoop up any hot coals that we
could and rushed to a cave.
>> Let's go to that cave
down yonder.
>> What cave?
Cave down here we have to go to.
>> They're behind us...
There we go.
>> There it is.
>> We're good.
>> Just run and go back and work
on everything else.
There you go.
>> What do you want to do?
You want to stay here or you
want to go help?
Both of us can't stay.
>> Oh, dude, no.
>> Ange, are you staying?
>> I'll stay.
I'll stay if you want
to go back to camp.
We can... whatever you want.
>> I talked to Ashlee a little
bit.
>> Yeah.
>> And I told her pretty much
that, you know, I was down
with any sort of alliance
'cause you guys really pulled
through for me last time.
>> I know.
>> Kim's not pulling her weight
as much as everybody else.
>> At the immunity challenge,
Kim didn't want to help
the team pull that chest.
So I'll tell you how it's going
to happen.
Kim is gone.
>> Oh, yeah, for sure.
>> And it's obvious to me
you're attracted to Kim, okay?
And right now, psychologically,
sociologically, I'm seeing Kim
as a threat, you know?
>> Yeah. I just... I mean,
I was thinking Ashlee,
to be honest.
She's-She's breaking down, man.
I can see it.
I mean, I can tell
she's breaking down.
>> She's not a threat,
though, at the moment.
>> James is definitely rubbing
me the wrong way.
He doesn't have the right
to come to me and say, "Oh,
listen, it's Kim over Ashlee."
Well, not to me it's not.
Ashlee has kind of changed
her frame of mind.
I can see her slowing down.
I mean at this point, let's vote
off our weakest link.
>> Hey, Steph.
>> What?
>> After kinda like thinking,
I think we push Ashlee.
>> Yeah?
>> I mean, just being honest
with you.
>> Honestly, Kim and Ashlee
are just...
they're about right here.
You know, one's up, one's down.
One's up, one's down.
So you gotta go with your gut
instinct.
>> But I'm telling you that we
need to break her and Jeff up
because...
>> I don't see what's wrong
with that, really, right now.
>> You don't?
But if they stay together,
they're going to go.
They're going to go to the end.
>> Mm, not necessarily.
>> I mean, she didn't even
try at the challenge.
She stood up there.
>> Yeah.
>> She wouldn't go down in the
water.
The bottom line is we have to
think of who's going to be
better for the team right now
so we don't have to go back
to Tribal Council.
Angie, myself, James and
Ashlee still want to vote Kim
off.
Bobby Jon is undecided.
So it's a complete mess,
because actually, now
it looks like four people
are voting against Kim
and four people are voting
against Ashlee,
so we're going to have a tie.
I don't even know
what happens in a tie.
>> What are you doing?
>> Dude, I don't even know.
>> I don't know now.
>> Is it me?
>> Between you and Ashlee.
>> Really? Who said me?
>> It's, like, the consensus.
Everybody.
>> I want to know.
If I'm going to get voted off,
I want somebody to tell me
that they're voting for me,
and I will respect the people
a heck of a lot more
if they can just be, like,
"Yes, I'm voting for you."
I don't want to frickin' go
home.
I don't think I should have to
go home.
But, J, look at me.
I want you to swear to God
that you'll tell me if you're
going to vote for me.
>> I'll tell you.
>> Okay.
>> I promise, okay?
>> Bobby Jon wasn't sure.
He thinks it's gonna be you,
but...
I'm totally not thinking,
like, smart at all.
>> Well, maybe they're trying to
do the same thing we're doing.
Those four in an alliance,
and then if one of us goes,
we're going to be picked off
one by one.
>> I really think it's going
to end up in a tie if everybody
sticks to where they're at right
now.
Obviously, you can't assume
anything in this game.
So they might do something
totally different, and I don't
know.
>> PROBST: Very subdued faces.
Tribal Council wasn't fun the
first time.
Not going to be any
more enjoyable tonight.
Well, first, let's start with
some of the good things.
Angie, from where I sit,
an amazing turnaround,
considering you were last
picked, thought you were nearly
out of this tribe, and then we
we get to this reward challenge
and you dominated.
Was there an impact with the
tribe?
Did they recognize that?
>> I think that they did
recognize.
I think that when somebody was
saying that I was a physical
weak link, I think that kind of
got into the heads of other
people, even though it wasn't
necessarily true.
>> PROBST: Well, here's the good
news.
You did win the reward
challenge.
And with that came fishing gear
and fire.
The bad news of what's happened
over the last couple of days,
you lost another immunity
challenge.
Kim, what was the reaction
when you got back to camp,
knowing you were going to come
back to Tribal Council
and vote somebody out?
>> I think it was actually
total devastation.
I mean, we've become
really, really close.
I don't think you're prepared
for how quickly
you bond with people.
I mean, I... at home you never
feel this way after, what, six
days with somebody?
But we rely on each other so
much.
>> PROBST: Jeff.
Any friendships?
Flirting? Adversaries?
Give me something.
>> Honestly, Kim and I have
gotten to know each other
a little bit more than I think
I've gotten to know
some of the other girls.
>> PROBST: Kim, when did you
feel the first initial seeds
of any attraction?
>> It's hot in here all of a
sudden.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Day one?
>> Actually, yes, it was day
one.
Because I couldn't sleep
and he was staying up, so...
>> PROBST: Steph.
Have you noticed Jeff and Kim?
>> Yeah, they hang out a lot.
They cuddle.
>> We've all noticed.
>> All jokes aside, it really is
nice to have someone laying next
to you when you're cold.
It's a big difference.
>> PROBST: The problem with
that, Jeff, is you get into a
game that is based on
social relationships and it's
about voting and numbers.
>> I see that completely,
but I think everybody here
understands that there's no
alliances being built here.
>> PROBST: Kim, obviously, you
must feel the same way.
>> Under my observations,
I hope that they understand
that it's not... I mean, it's
never crossed my mind that
that's going to change anything
or influence anything.
>> PROBST: It's never crossed
your mind that they might look
and say... "Well..."?
>> Not until now.
Really, in all honesty.
>> PROBST: James.
What are you basing your vote on
tonight?
>> I got my mind made up.
It's somebody that I think can't
hang with the rest of us,
they're lagging and they're...
ready to go home.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Steph, you're up.
>> Ashlee was the one that
picked me to be on this tribe,
so I just feel like I have to be
somewhat loyal to her right now.
>> I'm a man of my word,
and plus, you just bug
the hell out of me.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
...Kim.
Ashlee.
One vote Kim; one vote Ashlee.
Jeff.
One vote Kim; one vote Ashlee;
one vote Jeff.
Ashlee. It's two votes Ashlee.
Ashlee.
That's three votes Ashlee;
one vote Kim; one vote Jeff.
Second person voted
out of Survivor: Palau:
Ashlee.
Based on the votes cast,
four is enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Ashlee, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, I sense that tonight's
vote was tough.
I do believe you guys are a
tight tribe with a lot of good
energy, but my take?
Get a clear goal first,
then harness that energy.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> They're coming closer.
>> PROBST: Koror goes hunting.
>> There he is.
>> PROBST: Ulong faces a
setback.
>> I can barely put any weight
on it right now.
>> Everything I say,
you have some snotty remark...
>> PROBST: And Caryn and Katie
have it out.
>> Get off me!
>> She's completely lost it.
>> I'm just so incredibly
grateful to have had this
opportunity.
I'm not surprised
by the votes tonight.
I think that they all sensed
I was ready to go home.
The only regret I have
is that I did not use
the excuse that I was cold
to cuddle with Ibrehem
'cause he sure is a cutie.