>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> Your shoulder's right
on my head.
>> JEFF: A close relationship
developed at Koror.
>> Jennifer and Gregg have
definitely teamed off.
I mean, they've got to
to think we're stupid
if we can't tell that
they're together.
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa...
>> JEFF: Ulong got lost in a
storm.
>> I'm going back to camp.
>> Why are you going
back to camp by yourself?
>> Why can't I?
>> Angie wanted to quit.
She's one of those folks
that says, "I can't do this."
>> JEFF: At Koror, Willard's
work ethic was questioned when
he failed to tend to the fire.
>> Willard's been getting a
free ride, and he's been able
to play this game
a lot longer than he should.
>> JEFF: At the challenge...
Win or lose, both tribes
are going to Tribal Council
tonight.
The winning tribe will
vote somebody out.
They will then cross
to the jury side,
help themselves to some stew
and root beer and listen in
as the losing tribe
has their Tribal Council.
Ibrehem down.
Ibrehem failed to retrieve
a bottle.
>> Come on, Ib!
>> JEFF: Koror wins reward.
>> Get on the raft!
>> JEFF: At Ulong...
>> I can't believe we lost.
>> JEFF: Ibrehem's mistake was
hard to overlook.
>> We had it in the bag.
Then Ibrehem, we lost because of
him.
He's history.
>> JEFF: Jubilation turned
to paranoia, as Koror faced
their first Tribal Council.
>> He's out, right?
>> Yeah.
( indistinct voices )
>> Don't tell anyone.
>> I won't.
>> JEFF: And Gregg let Coby
in on his plan with Jenn.
Once Willard and Caryn are gone,
it becomes seven people,
me, Jenn, you and Janu.
Then we start picking
them off.
>> I'm very excited.
I love that the game is going
to a new level.
I can't wait.
>> JEFF: At Koror's first
Tribal Council...
Fifth person voted out
of Survivor Palau...
Willard was voted out.
The tribe has spoken.
Koror, go ahead and pull off
the cover.
Koror then dug into their beef
stew reward in front of a
dejected Ulong tribe.
>> Oh!
>> It was really close today.
We really needed this.
>> It seems like all I've heard
today is "Wow, we could have
really been eating that beef
stew right now," like that's
the end of the game,
like beef stew is it.
>> JEFF: And with Ibrehem on
the chopping block,
there was one more surprise.
Koror, you are going
to vote to give immunity
to one person from Ulong.
Koror voted and gave immunity
to Ibrehem.
With a wrench thrown into
Ulong's plans, Bobby Jon and
Angie each received two votes.
We have a tie.
Stephenie had first voted for
Bobby Jon, but in the tiebreaker
she changed her vote, and Angie
was voted out.
The tribe has spoken.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
♪ ♪
>> That may have been the
craziest Tribal Council
I've ever been to.
From walking in, believing
that I was going
to be voted off,
but then the tide got turned
and the other tribe ended up
giving me immunity.
And, uh, someone else ended up
getting voted off instead of me.
>> I think for the next
challenge, not only do we
need to have great listening
skills, because I'm also...
>> Yeah, everybody needs to
listen.
>> I mean, like...
>> Keep your ears open
and listen to your teammates.
>> Tonight at Tribal Council,
Ib got the immunity.
So, um, Angie was the one that
ended up going.
But you know, he knew was gonna
get voted off,
and he knows he's going next,
'cause I'm not changing my mind.
So we'll see what happens.
>> I was pissed at you, really.
You wasn't paying
attention today.
That was your problem.
>> Okay.
>> Okay?
You cost us the game because
you didn't pay attention.
All you had to do was
yank on the bottle.
>> Yeah, you're right.
>> You were yanking
on the rope.
>> No, ain't none of us perfect.
>> You should have been at
least honest and, uh...
>> About what?
>> ...told us that you couldn't
dive down deep enough
to get the bottle.
>> Didn't I tell you I was
honest about it?
I told you, if you was
listening, I said I dove down
I was at two bottles,
and I tried to pull the rope.
>> Yeah, all we know is
you went down three times,
didn't come up with a bottle.
>> Bottom line is,
we just need to win now.
'Cause we really can't afford to
lose anybody else.
I mean for real.
>> And you need to focus,
you know.
>> James just kind of put
Ibrehem on the spot.
I mean...
I don't agree with that,
you know.
I mean, we win as a team
and lose as a team.
Yeah, he-he missed the bottle,
and we didn't win the beef stew.
I mean, whatever, you know.
You can't get over
beef and stew?
Please.
>> A lot of times I'm able to
get off on my own away by
myself and actually do my
prayers.
I think if things would have
just stayed on track at Tribal,
I'm pretty sure I-I probably
wouldn't be here right now.
I don't know.
The way things happen,
I almost think
God had a hand in it.
I feel like I'm definitely
meant to be here.
I think you appreciate things
a little more when it's almost
taken away from you,
so I think I got
a whole new grasp on it.
>> Last night was the first
Tribal Council, and we had to
vote somebody off, which
ended up being Willard.
And then, we got to eat our
stew.
Right away, you started, you
felt this rush of energy back.
And the crew woke up
this morning very charged up
and refreshed.
And it's just another day
in paradise today.
>> Idle hands are the devil's
plaything, you know.
You know what?
It's a different day, you know.
We all got fed,
everyone's got a little energy,
and everyone's doing a project.
Today is a day just to kind of
do something to save ourselves
some work down the road.
>> What do you think?
>> That's pretty.
That's so cool.
Camp Koror had craft day.
Well, just Katie;
everybody else was working.
Didn't help with the fire,
didn't go hunt,
didn't go do anything.
But she made necklaces,
God love her.
Actually, more of a headband.
>> I feel great, I really do.
I thought it'd be harder than
this.
And it will be,
and I'm prepared for that.
So I think that if you keep
that state of mind,
then you can survive.
>> It's pretty.
>> So what do you do after
you get the three...?
>> You just start
tying them together.
>> I would like to see Katie
work a little harder
and move a little faster.
It appears that she's just here
to entertain.
She sings, she's cheerful,
she makes a lot of jokes.
But what is her role here?
I don't know.
>> I'm so sad!
>> Boo-hoo!
( shouting )
>> My name is Angie, and I can
smell the stew.
( laughter )
>> I'm Bobby Jon.
I love everyone,
and I look like Jesus Christ.
( laughter )
Waaah...!
>> Open the box.
Ooh.
( gasps )
Pringle!
Tree mail!
>> Tree mail!
>> Guess what it has on it?
>> Guess!
It starts with a P!
>> And ends with a "le"!
Pringle!
>> Pringle?
Oh.
>> "Ready, aim, fire.
"You'll each get a shot.
>> Yeah!
>> "Make sure it's a good one,
you'll be bummed if it's not.
"No strength required,
a steady hand to compete.
See the wonders
"of these islands
and give your taste buds
a treat."
( cheering )
>> So, it sounds like
it's going to be some sort
of shooting competition.
We don't know whether
or not it's bow and arrow,
we don't know if it's slingshot,
gun.
But, yeah, we really
want to win this.
( all growling )
>> JEFF: Come on in, Koror.
Koror getting your first look
at the new Ulong tribe.
Angie voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> Ready for today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: There are 16
tribe-colored tiles, eight for
Koror, eight for Ulong.
Using a replica of a 50-caliber
small-class cannon,
you're going to attempt
to knock out your tribe tiles.
First tribe to knock out all
eight of their tribe tiles
wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Well, it started this
morning with your tree mail.
Pringles is part of your reward.
The winning tribe will leave
here and you will board
a very unique, one-of-a-kind
Japanese boat.
On board, you'll have
Pringles and mai-tais.
>> Oh, my God!
>> JEFF: While you're relaxing,
you'll cruise out to a body of
water called Jellyfish Lake.
It is literally home
to millions of jellyfish.
You're gonna snorkel
with the jellyfish.
And the good news is,
they can't hurt you.
They have lost their necessity
and their ability to sting.
You've never seen anything
like this.
You'll be rejuvenated,
get some food in your belly,
couple of drinks--
could be a whole new game.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> Yes, sir.
>> JEFF: All right, Koror, you
have four extra members-- you're
sitting four people out--
who's it gonna be?
>> Katie, Janu, Jenn and me.
>> JEFF: Have a seat on the
bench; we'll get started.
>> JEFF: All right, after
rock-paper-scissor, Ulong, you
won the right to go first.
Once you establish your order,
keep it.
Ready, aim, and whenever you're
ready, Bobby Jon.
Low.
Gregg.
Let's go, Gregg.
Take a little while
to get used to this sight.
>> Almost.
>> JEFF: James.
You shoot a lot of guns?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Whenever you're ready.
Ooh.
>> Wow!
>> JEFF: Just misses.
Coby. Still no score.
>> Go, farm boy.
>> JEFF: Coby could put Koror
in the lead.
Just misses.
Ibrehem.
Take your aim.
Learn from the people
who've gone before you.
Low.
Tom.
( loud cheering )
>> JEFF: Tom.
The first to hit a tile.
Koror leads, one-zip.
All right, Steph.
>> JEFF: That's it!
Steph drills it!
We're tied, one-one.
Caryn getting her first shot
at the gun.
Just misses.
Bobby Jon coming back up.
Bobby Jon
connects for Ulong!
Ulong leads two, one.
( indistinct talking )
Gregg could tie it up for Koror.
That's how you do it!
We're tied up at two-two.
James.
Ooh.
Coby could put Koror
in the lead.
Just misses.
Ibrehem.
>> Yes!
>> Nice!
>> JEFF: Ibrehem connects.
Three-two, Ulong leads.
Tom had no troubles
his first time.
Let's see if he can tie it up.
Ooh. Just misses.
Steph.
>> JEFF: She does!
Ulong leads, four-two;
they're halfway there.
Caryn makes it three for Koror.
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: That's five-three,
Ulong.
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: Gregg keeps Koror in
it.
James, you are oh-fer.
>> You ain't lyin'!
I'm doggin' it today, ain't I?
>> JEFF: Still dry.
>> Still dry.
>> JEFF: Takes his aim...
Tom up for Koror.
Ulong with a five-four lead.
Steph would like
to increase that.
And she does!
Ulong leads, six-four.
Ulong with only two tiles left.
You're pretty good
with that gun.
( inhales sharply )
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: Caryn connects!
Koror with five.
>> You got it.
>> JEFF: And he connects!
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: Ulong leads
seven-five-- they're one tile
away from reward.
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: Gregg connects for
Koror!
We are at seven-six.
Here's where things stand.
One tile left.
Knock it out, you win.
Miss and Koror is still alive.
Low and to the right.
Koror still in this.
Coby, you need to connect
to keep you alive.
Ulong leads, seven-six.
You like this pressure,
don't you?
Coby does it!
We are tied, seven-seven.
Ibrehem, if you connect,
you will have eight,
Koror will get last shot
to tie it up.
Ooh.
Just misses to the right,
opens the door for Koror.
Tom, because Ulong went first,
you guys get last shot.
You have one tile left-- that
means if you hit it, you win it.
Pringles, mai-tais,
Jellyfish Lake.
For the win.
Ooh!
Just misses.
Steph, you have one tile left--
hit it, you'll have eight
tiles, Koror will get last shot.
Steph does it again!
Ulong with eight tiles;
Koror gets their last shot.
Pressure is on Caryn.
It's very simple, Caryn--
hit your tile,
you force a tiebreaker;
miss, Ulong wins reward.
It's all on you.
>> You got it, Caryn.
>> JEFF: Get your aim.
Misses low to the left!
Ulong wins reward!
( shouting, cheering )
>> Pringles and mai-tais!
>> JEFF: Koror, something
you haven't experienced
much of in 13 days out here:
defeat.
I got nothing for you.
Ulong, I don't know if a tribe
has ever needed a reward
like you guys.
Great shooting, Steph.
Pringles, mai-tai,
Jellyfish Lake.
>> We won the reward;
I freaked out.
It was just such a nice feeling
to know what it's like
to win again.
I mean, we've been losing so
much, and I hate that feeling.
Hello, Pringles and mai-tais...
Oh, my God, I see...
( mumbles inaudibly )
I knew that we needed this
to boost our spirits and morale,
and it... it basically, it was
a whole new chapter for us.
>> Look at that.
>> Oh, hell, yeah!
( groans )
Let's have a toast.
Oh, I get the pink one, too.
>> Everybody, get you a bottle.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Okay.
>> Look-- Survivor Pringles.
>> Ah.
>> This is cool.
>> It's trivia.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Yeah.
All right, ready?
"Which Survivor: Pearl Islands
castaway has a daughter
named Raya?"
>> Rupert.
>> Yes.
>> The Pringles had questions
about other Survivor seasons,
which that was kind of neat.
And we were all kind of, like,
reading our questions,
answer 'em, eating the Pringles.
>> "Which three Survivor
all-stars won cars during the
show?"
>> Who was it?
>> Boston Rob and Amber.
>> And?
>> Shii Ann.
"Who won more, men or women?"
>> Men.
>> Women.
Isn't that amazing?
Pretty damn good.
We got to have another toast.
Think so.
Name of this toast is called
"From here on out."
From here on out...
>> We win.
>> We're buddies.
>> And keep going...
going with the tide.
>> Oh, I think we made it.
>> After we climbed
to the top of the mountain,
we see this lake,
and it's just...
it's just crystal clear.
It's just amazing to know that
you're about to go somewhere
where all these jellyfish
are at, and none of them can
sting you 'cause they lost their
stinging tentacles,
because they're in fresh water,
and they've been there
for millions of years.
>> Let's do this.
You're swimming in the water,
and all of a sudden you see,
oh, there's a jellyfish,
and then five minutes later,
you're with millions, and...
they're just all just coming at
you.
It's just...
It's kind of like
a euphoric type of feeling.
And I just kind of wanted
to cherish every second,
'cause I was at a place
in this world where I won't ever
go again.
>> The win for us today
was a huge boost of morale.
We feel confident now.
We feel healthy,
we feel strong.
And we feel, you know, happy.
We feel like a tribe again.
( crackling thunder )
>> It's so sandy.
It's in my eyes,
it's in my mouth.
>> Is Tom's sand still up?
>> The sand is still up.
The wind is coming
directly at it.
>> You a little worried?
>> Yeah.
>> This isn't going to go
anywhere, there's no way.
I'd like to see 'em try.
( thunder crackling )
( whooping and laughter )
>> We had a, uh, a rainstorm
that kicked in, but now the
wind has picked up to a point.
I mean, this-this feels
like about a 40-mile-an-hour
wind right now.
It's really gusting hard.
Oh, God!
Are you, like, kidding me?
( rumbling thunder )
>> I don't know what the hell
that was, but it wasn't
paradise in Palau,
that's for sure.
>> Uh-uh.
>> That was.
That was absolute torture.
>> Last night was the first
night I think that I've ever had
where I felt so vulnerable.
I just felt very alone
and scared.
But, I mean, I ended up
getting through the night,
but it kind of just has
lingered on into the day.
>> Hang in there.
This is...
It's a bad day.
I feel the same way.
I'm so far away from
my family today that I'm down.
>> I feel like crap.
I'm just... I don't want
to get out of bed either.
It's, uh...
It's a bad place to be,
but let today be a bad day.
>> It's so hard.
>> It is hard.
It's very hard.
>> I'm so depleted.
>> You've already passed
your worst fear
of going home early.
You're going to make the merge.
I think you're going
to be on the jury,
and if most of us aren't
careful, we're going to be the
jury voting on you.
>> I don't have the strength.
>> You do.
>> I don't, I'm telling you.
>> Yeah, you don't have it
today, I agree with you.
You don't have it today,
but you have it.
>> Janu is losing it.
She gets totally caught up
in her head,
and she's like in the cocoon
in the hammock.
And everything is always
dramatic with Janu.
So I thought I was
the drama queen, but...
apparently not.
>> Rice?
>> No.
>> Is it heavy?
>> Yeah.
>> "This flag and box
belong to your enemy.
"Stop.
Your enemy has your flag
"and box also.
Stop.
"You must secure the flag
inside this box using only
"the ropes provided.
Stop.
"Make this box impenetrable.
"Bring the secured box
to the challenge.
Stop."
So who knows how...?
>> Tie good knots.
>> Tree mail is a big old chest,
flag in it and a bunch of rope.
And we have to make it
impenetrable.
Well, I know a few things
about knots.
I've got a plan for you.
I learned this in the Navy.
They're not going to find a
knot.
You can tug on it all you want.
>> Oh.
>> Cool.
>> All right, James.
We're going to let you
do the tying, 'cause...
I'm not good at tying.
>> James says he was in the
Navy.
We spent a lot of time tying
this one knot that he says like
that when you pull on it,
that it's just going to get
real, real tighter.
He took the lead.
And he acted like he knew
what he was doing,
so, you know, I followed.
>> Wait a minute.
What the hell?
Where's the end?
>> Regulators!
>> I'm pretty sure
this is ours the taking,
so... we're gonna win.
>> JEFF: All right,
first things first.
Janu, give it up.
Immunity is back up for grabs.
All right, today's immunity
challenge began this morning
with your tree mail.
You each received
a footlocker and some rope.
Inside the footlocker
was the opposing tribe's flag.
You were instructed to use that
rope and make the footlocker
as impenetrable as you could.
The challenge continues.
Now you'll have 20 minutes
to swim out, retrieve
three bundles of lumber,
build a fortress
around this footlocker
to make it even more difficult
to get into.
After 20 minutes, we'll stop,
switch sides and each tribe
will attempt to undo
what the other tribe
has just done.
First tribe to release their
flag, secure it to the flag pole
and raise it to the top
wins immunity.
Koror, the four people
who sat out the last challenge
are in this one--
Jenn, Katie, Janu and Ian.
Everybody else take
a spot on the bench.
Let's go.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Ulong sending three people out.
Koror sending just two.
Katie and Janu adding more
knots.
James getting a game plan for
Ulong.
Starts with keeping his toga on.
>> Ready?
Pull.
I got this one.
>> JEFF: Bobby Jon and Steph
coming back with the first load.
Ibrehem waiting in the middle.
I'll pass it to you.
>> Yeah.
Tell James to get close to
shore.
>> JEFF: Katie and Janu already
doing a lot of rope work.
The more knots,
the more difficult
it's going to be to untie.
James in no hurry at all.
Ulong coming back with
all three bundles at once.
James gives up on the toga.
Jenn back with a load for Koror.
You have 20 minutes
to get this thing
as impenetrable as possible.
Need to pick it up.
Ulong starting to work
on their fortress.
>> Good knot.
Make sure it's on the other end,
too.
>> JEFF: Steph getting
her teeth involved.
Ian back with the last load
of lumber for Koror.
Koror finally getting to work
on their fortress.
>> JEFF: Ten minutes down,
ten minutes to go.
>> Come on.
>> JEFF: Five minutes left.
Five minutes, we will switch
sides, and you will have to
untie what the other tribe has
done.
One minute left.
Ulong has used every piece
of rope they have.
Koror still has
quite a bit of rope left.
Ulong shoving every piece
of lumber they can.
Koror doing the same thing.
Two big disaster piles.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Everybody stop.
All right, on my "go,"
you will switch sides
and start untying.
First tribe to get
their flag free
and up the flag pole
wins immunity.
Be tigers, guys!
Survivors ready?
Go!
Now we're going to find out
who did a better job
of securing their footlocker.
No time limit here.
It is simply
the first tribe to finish.
Both tribes
making good progress.
Koror used a lot of wood
and a lot of knots.
Steph not impressed
with Koror's knots.
Ulong appears to have
a bit of a lead.
Ian takes care of the big rope
with no trouble.
>> But that's what's in it.
>> Keep doing that.
>> JEFF: Ulong starting to
slow down.
Koror getting closer.
>> TOM: Good, Koror!
>> There you go!
Yeah!
>> JEFF: Koror getting very
close.
Koror has their footlocker!
Come on.
( indistinct shouting )
Now you've got to untie it.
Ulong getting closer to
releasing their footlocker.
You guys need to keep moving.
Pull, pull, pull!
You're waltzing.
>> Slow and steady.
Just maintain that work.
>> JEFF: Both tribes working
on their footlocker.
This is where all your earlier
knot tying is going to pay off.
Ulong working together well.
Got to get that footlocker open.
Koror getting closer and closer.
Ulong with a lot of knots
to get undone,
but they're moving quickly.
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: Ulong still working
strong.
You're still in it.
Koror getting closer and closer.
Ulong not giving up.
Immunity at stake.
Tribal Council awaits.
Somebody going home.
Koror literally down
to their last few knots.
>> GREGG: There you go!
>> JEFF: Koror has their
flag free.
Got to get it up the flag pole!
>> GREGG: There we are!
>> JEFF: Koror wins their fifth
straight immunity challenge!
All right, Ulong.
>> Oh, great job.
>> Nice.
>> Great job.
>> JEFF: Koror, you have yet to
lose an immunity challenge.
( whooping )
>> JEFF: No Tribal Council,
nobody going home.
Ulong, you have yet to win
an immunity challenge.
Next Tribal Council,
somebody going home.
This tribe will be
down to three.
Head on back.
See you at Tribal Council
tomorrow night.
>> We ended up losing
another immunity challenge.
Ulong hasn't won an immunity
challenge yet this whole game.
When it comes to
tonight at Tribal,
the only criteria
I'm going to go with
is whoever I think
has done the worst
out of all these
immunity challenges.
So it will most likely
be for James.
>> Ibrehem has overstayed
his welcome.
He was meant to go last time.
And by the grace of Allah,
he didn't go.
Well, my god says he is today.
I got two votes the other
night at Tribal Council,
and I know Angie was one.
but I thought Stephenie was the
other, but it wasn't Stephenie.
I'm thinking it was James,
and it was male handwriting.
So I'm thinking James threw
a dart at me and I'm going
to throw one at him.
>> She had to go.
We couldn't lose you.
I don't like to lie,
but this was in the midst of we
were deciding who we were
gonna vote out tonight,
so there's no way in hell I
could have told him the truth.
So I said, "I swear to God
it wasn't me."
I...
It was a close one.
>> Yeah, it was.
>> I feel really bad
lying about it,
but if I would have
told him the truth,
they would have
voted me off tonight.
He would never
be able to trust me.
Either way, somebody's going to
get their feelings hurt.
>> Yeah.
I swear to God, I voted
for Angie, though.
That's right.
>> So I said to Bobby Jon,
"Well, what if it's a tie?
"Then what are we gonna do?
We're gonna put
our butts on the line?"
And he assured me that
he wanted to make an alliance
with me that if I vote
for James tonight, he wants
to vote Ibrehem out next.
Okay.
I'll vote for James with you.
>> Right.
>> That's only if you promise
if the three of us are still
here, you and I will
go to the end...
>> We'll go to the end.
and we'll vote Ib off.
Yeah, we'll do that.
'Cause I think we
deserve it the best.
>> Yeah, I know we do.
>> Okay.
Well, then, that's what we'll
do.
>> At this point in the game,
I'm looking in the future,
and I don't think
I can get to the end
with Ibrehem.
So, it will definitely be
me and Stephenie all the way to
the end.
If she's playing me,
we'll find out,
but I don't think she is.
>> I'm between two sides
right now.
Because I can stick with James
and it will be a tie,
or go with Bobby Jon and Ib,
vote off James,
and then persuade Bobby Jon
to stick with his word,
and next time, Ib will go.
I really don't know
where I stand right now.
>> JEFF: James?
>> Yo.
>> JEFF: You have not
won a single immunity challenge.
>> I tell you what...
>> JEFF: Tell me something.
When we hear the word
"immunity," I think we
subconsciously
sabotage ourselves.
>> JEFF: Well, let's talk about
that.
Do you guys think you gave 100%
the last immunity challenge?
I mean, I sat there and watched.
>> Oh, yeah...
>> JEFF: Steph and Bobby Jon
swam out.
Ibrehem took a leisurely stroll
to the middle, doing what,
I'm still not sure.
And you sat back there
messing with your skirt
for two, three, four minutes.
>> Wow.
>> JEFF: That's when
you lost the challenge.
>> Well, that's not what held
us up.
>> JEFF: Ibrehem, last Tribal
Council it looked like you were
this close to being gone.
Have you ever thought,
these first few days out here,
"Maybe I'm just not cut out for
this game?
>> Uh, actually, I've never
thought like that.
Um...
It's really opened my eyes
to what I can do, rather than
what I can't handle.
>> JEFF: James, if you hold
the same criteria that
you were holding to Ibrehem
from last Tribal Council,
do you think it's fair
to base a vote simply on how
you performed in a challenge?
>> No, it's not fair to go ahead
and just base my vote
directly towards a challenge.
It's camp life, personality.
Do I get along with this person?
Do I have personal feelings
for this person? You know.
>> JEFF: Steph, you guys
have to be fighting for
your own lives at this point.
This tribe is almost done.
>> We're almost out of numbers
here.
But the fact remains,
that I want to win
at least one immunity.
I mean, I don't want to leave
here being that tribe
that never won immunity.
That's like a disgrace.
>> JEFF: Bobby Jon?
>> Yes, sir.
>> JEFF: Do you trust these
people in your tribe?
>> If you don't trust 'em,
you shouldn't be
in a tribe with them.
You can't have a tribe
if you don't trust people,
and I do trust
every one of them.
>> JEFF: Steph, do you trust
these three guys?
>> I do.
>> JEFF: Somebody here
gives you their word,
you can go to the bank with it?
>> Absolutely.
And, uh, when I get
someone's word and I give them
my word, I hope that they, you
know, take it, and, so,
I do trust them.
>> JEFF: You three guys are all
from, basically, the same part
of the country, right?
>> Pretty much.
>> Alabama.
>> JEFF: Steph.
A little bit of a concern
that if you're looking
for some way to divide
this tribe, three guys, one
girl, all from the same part
of the world, and you.
>> That paranoia sets in for me
every time we come here.
But, um, the fact remains
that I've worked my butt off,
and I've done the best I could,
and I've done really well so
far, so I just feel like
it's really not my time yet,
and I just hope that
they see that, too.
>> JEFF: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Bobby Jon, you're up.
( whispering ): Sorry, Ibrehem,
you and I, we just don't get
along, we clash.
It's time for you to go.
Bye.
Sorry, brother.
♪ ♪
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> JEFF: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave
the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
James.
Ibrehem.
One vote James,
one vote Ibrehem.
James.
Two votes James,
one vote Ibrehem.
I'll read the last vote.
Ibrehem.
We're tied:
two votes Ibrehem,
two votes James.
Let me remind you how
a tiebreaker's going to work.
Ibrehem and James,
you will not vote.
Steph, Bobby Jon, you will vote;
you're voting for one of
two people, Ibrehem or James.
This is your last chance
to change your vote.
It's time to revote.
Bobby Jon, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out
will be asked to leave
the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
James.
Seventh person voted out
of Survivor: Palau...
James.
>> ( softly ): I'm sorry.
I had to.
>> I understand, y'all.
>> JEFF: James, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, Ulong, this is a first:
a tribe of three.
Six straight Tribal Councils.
Maybe tonight's vote
made a difference.
If not, we'll be seeing you
here real soon.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor...
a relationship gets
complicated...
>> Their little romance
could be a monkey wrench
that we don't see coming.
>> JEFF: Bobby Jon scores for
Ulong...
>> Yeah, good job.
>> Getting that fish felt like
making an extra point, you know,
to win the game.
( cheering )
>> JEFF: ...while Tom makes a
slam dunk.
How's that for a shot?!
It wasn't my time to go.
I didn't feel like it, you know?
My gut told me nobody's going to
vote me off.
My gut failed me,
and I'm sad and depressed,
you know?
But I've accomplished things
that not many people
can say they have,
and that makes me proud.
I am glad that I got a chance
to go on Survivor and see if
I had what it takes.