>> JEFF PROBST: Previously ON
on Survivor:
>> What the hell was that?
>> PROBST: After Janu shocked
her tribe by quitting the game,
Koror's plan to oust Stephenie
was out in the open.
>> STEPHENIE: I don't know who
to trust.
I don't know who to talk to.
I almost don't want to talk
to anybody.
>> PROBST: But Stephenie's
presence in the game put
the men on edge.
>> Stephenie progressing
in this game means that Koror
falls apart.
>> PROBST: Tom was also feeling
vulnerable.
>> I'm pleading for my life.
My strength in the challenges,
it's part of what got us to
this point.
>> PROBST: But the women saw
an opportunity and a plan
was hatched.
>> I think it's an awesome idea.
>> Who would be the first one
you'd want off?
>> You want to think I'm
a threat?
I'll show you how threatening
I am.
>> PROBST: Before the immunity
challenge, Tom turned to Caryn.
>> I think that we do have some
kind of a sympathetic thing
going where we're going to
look out for each other.
It was a good move on my part
to be friends with Caryn.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, the pressure was on.
There are five tiles for
each of you.
First person to break all five
of their tiles wins immunity.
But Ian was handed victory
when Tom took out his last tile.
Ian wins immunity.
>> Thank you, guys.
>> PROBST: Back at camp,
Katie approached Caryn about
the women's alliance.
Stick with the women
and take out the men?
>> PROBST: Caryn leaked the
information.
>> What do the girls think?
>> Trying to figure out
which side to take out.
>> PROBST: So Ian confronted
Katie when he learned of
her plan.
>> Caryn is spreading that
you're trying to get all the
girls against the guys.
>> I just hate for it to be such
a sweep and Tom just takes
the whole thing and none of
us have a chance.
>> PROBST: All hope for the
women's alliance was crushed...
It's already been too much
of the Stephenie show.
Stephenie needs to go.
Too much of the Stephenie show.
>> PROBST: But Steph still clung
to hope.
>> I've said my piece,
I planted my seed.
If they're smart, Tom will be
the next one to go.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
although Caryn received one
vote, Koror stuck together.
The third member of our jury,
Steph.
And Stephenie, the only
remaining Ulong member,
was finally voted out.
The tribe has spoken.
Six are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
(man groaning)
>> Poor girl.
Did you see her face?
She was probably stressing out.
>> It was horrible. I know.
>> I felt bad.
>> Stephenie was the one
voted off.
I thought that it could
have been me last night.
I wouldn't blame them.
If I was playing against me,
I'd want me out of here, too,
but they didn't do it;
it was a relief.
They're holding true to the
five, and would I like to
believe that it will continue
to do that.
>> Everything's good;
everything's good.
>> I'm going to tell you I've
been trying to think of
different things.
I'm up all night running
scenarios.
>> Me, too.
>> Caryn and I spoke on the way
to tree mail.
She's more nervous than a long-
tailed cat in a roomful of
rocking chairs, at this point.
She knows that she's outside
of an alliance of five,
so she feels she's next.
I can't step out from five to
side with one right now.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And what you've got to do
is pull your own savior;
your salvation.
>> I've been telling Tom and Ian
that Gregg and Jenn need to be
split, and he said he knew that,
but that he could not turn
against the five people that he
had the alliance with, so...
I am definitely the most
vulnerable of the six remaining,
no question about it.
I'm just hoping and praying
that something happens.
Otherwise, I'm going home.
>> Scamper, scamper, scamper.
We got tree mail.
>> We're up, we're up, we're up.
>> "Care for a bit of R&R?
To be pampered would be nice."
>> ALL: Oh!
"To get the VIP treatment, some
island knowledge is the price."
>> "You'll soon know who your
friends are.
In love and war, all is fair."
>> "But there can only be one
winner, the one who keeps
their name up in the air."
>> Oh, man.
>> It sounds like, uh...
What we've been waiting for,
Jenn.
>> I know.
>> Everybody wants this.
>> Katie and I promised each
other, if we won a challenge,
we'd take each other if we have
the ability, and that's what
we're gonna today do.
>> Oh, my God. Oh, God.
I'm fighting hard for this one.
>> Me, too.
>> PROBST: Come on in!
We are down to six.
For today's reward challenge,
I'm going to ask you a series
of questions about Palau and
Micronesia.
Every time you answer a question
correctly, you earn the right to
drop another tribe member's
torch closer to the water.
After three drops on any one
tribe member's flame, that flame
goes in the water; they're out
of the challenge.
Last person left standing,
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
(horn blowing)
>> Look at that.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Double-decker.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> For your reward, you will
board a luxury yacht, you'll
get a fresh shower, then you
will feast.
You'll spend the night
on the yacht.
You will return to your beach
tomorrow-- hopefully
rejuvenated, re-energized,
to get you through these last
few days.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Take a spot.
Let's go.
All right, pick up the cubes;
we'll get started.
First question:
"Palau is famous for its green,
"mushroom-shaped islands
"known as: A) Stone islands,
B) Rock islands,
or C) Mushroom islands."
Correct answer is:
"B) Rock islands."
Everybody got it right.
Tom, you're up first.
>> Oh, no.
I didn't want to be first to
start this nastiness.
>> PROBST: Gregg takes the first
hit.
>> We'll even it out.
(chuckles)
>> PROBST: Jenn, you're up.
Who is Jenn going to hit?
Caryn takes her first hit.
Ian.
(laughs)
(weak laugh)
>> Whoa.
> PROBST: Caryn takes her
second hit.
Every reward we get, Caryn gets
all the food.
Caryn, you get to pay somebody
back right now.
Heading over to Katie.
Katie takes her first hit.
Gregg.
>> Tom.
>> PROBST: A little payback?
>> Little payback, that's it.
>> I would expect no less.
>> PROBST: Tom takes his first
hit.
Katie.
>> I'm out.
>> Surprise, surprise, surprise.
You also got a cheeseburger,
Caryn.
>> PROBST: Wow. Just like that.
>> Let's try to still be nice.
> PROBST: Caryn's out in the
first round and not happy.
Next question:
"In the early days of Palau,
stone was used as a form
of money.
The largest stone weighed up to:
"A) Five pounds;
"B) Ten pounds, C) 100 pounds,
or D) 10,000 pounds."
Correct answer is:
"D) 10,000 pounds."
>> Damn.
>> "Five tons."
Tom is the only one who got it
right.
Make your move.
>> Keep with an all-boy theme
on this one, and, uh...
>> No, don't do that.
>> I'm sorry, my friend.
>> PROBST: Ian takes his first
hit, courtesy of Tom.
Next question:
"The islands of Palau are
encompassed in the north Pacific
Ocean and which other body of
water?
"A) The Indonesian Delta,
"B) The Bay of Guam,
or C) The Philippine Sea."
Correct answer is:
"C) Philippine Sea."
Everybody has it right.
Everybody gets a shot.
Tom, you're up.
>> Just to level the playing
field.
>> PROBST: Jenn takes her
first hit.
Chance for payback to Tom.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Not even thinking
twice.
Tom, one hit away from being
out.
Ian could put Tom out of this
challenge right now.
>> And that's what I'm gonna do.
>> Sorry, buddy.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Tom takes a big dip
and a seat on the bench.
He's out of the challenge.
Everybody left in is even
at this point.
Gregg, lots of choices.
>> It's an easy one.
Sorry, "E."
>> PROBST: Ian takes his second
hit.
One hit away from being
out of the competition.
>> This is tough.
>> PROBST: Katie could put Ian
on the bench right here.
>> Don't let it come back to
haunt you.
>> He's out and can't vote
for you if you get him.
>> I'm getting you next.
>> Good point, good point.
>> Just so you know.
>> Would you hate me?
>> Yes.
>> Katie, no way.
>> Sorry.
>> You got to spare yourself.
>> You've got to spare yourself.
>> It's true.
>> Come over here, buddy.
>> PROBST: Ian is shocked,
and Ian is out of challenge.
>> I'm sorry, Ian.
>> Shot to the heart.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Next question--
"Palau lies in which direction
relative to the equator?"
"A) north, "B) south, C) east
or D) west"?
The correct answer is...
A) north.
Jenn has it wrong.
Gregg, Katie have it right.
Seven degrees north of the
equator.
>> That's why it's so damn hot.
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: Gregg, your shot.
>> Come on, not me.
>> PROBST: Your choices are
Jenn, Katie.
>> Damn!
>> I didn't take you out.
I could have, but I didn't.
>> Yeah.
>> That was a deal made, right?
>> It sounded like it.
I heard a promise.
>> Is that horrible if I hit
you, Jenn?
You'll never live it down, ever.
>> PROBST: Wait, Gregg.
>> Yeah.
Did you just ask permission?
>> Yes, he did.
>> Wow.
>> Is it okay, dear?
>> What a...
>> Gregg, be a man.
>> Don't do it, Gregg.
>> I can't believe you're doing
that.
>> You said, "I'll save you."
>> If you hit me, she's going
to hit me, too, I'll be out.
>> PROBST: Wow.
>> You suck, Gregg.
>> PROBST: Gregg hits Katie.
Katie comes back and hits Gregg,
and no smile on that face.
Interesting how that works.
Jenn is now in the lead.
Gregg and Katie down to their
last drop.
Jenn still has two hits.
True or false...
"Palau was the first nation in
the world to issue the Elvis
Presley postage stamp."
Correct answer is true.
Gregg got it right,
Jenn got it right.
Katie got it wrong.
Jenn, you're up.
>> Sorry, Katie.
>> Don't.
>> I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: Katie is out of the
competition, takes a seat on
the bench.
Gregg's only choice is Jenn.
>> At least he didn't ask.
>> PROBST: You both have one hit
left.
One person gets it right, and
the other person gets it wrong,
that's it.
"The coconut crabs which inhabit
the islands of Palau have the
special ability to do what after
they eat?
"A) change color;
B) leap up to three feet;
or C) replicate themselves?"
For reward, make your choice.
Jenn says B.
>> That is wrong.
>> Damn.
>> PROBST: Gregg says "A) change
That is right.
Gregg, make your final hit.
Gregg has no choice.
>> Oh, damn.
>> Sorry, Jenn.
>> PROBST: Takes Jenn, puts her
out of the challenge.
Gregg wins reward.
>> Sorry.
>> Good job, Gregg.
>> PROBST: Yacht, shower...
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: ...massage,
big feast.
Obviously it wouldn't be much
fun alone.
>> Oh!
So pick one person to join you.
>> Sorry, guys.
Jenn, let's go.
>> Oh!
Thank you.
>> Ooh...
>> PROBST: I'm sure you guys
will have a good time together.
And two is very fun, but three
is a party.
Pick one more person.
>> Oh, God!
>> Oh!
>> Sorry, man.
>> Katie.
(cheering)
>> You are forgiven.
>> Hey, guys, I'm so sorry.
I will, uh...
I will pay you back.
>> Oh, no, we'll pay you back.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: Tom, Ian, Caryn, head
on back to camp.
All right, guys, your yacht is
waiting.
Have a good night.
That's the icing on the cake.
We didn't come here for the
icing.
We came for the cake.
Let's go talk.
I have an idea.
>> You do?
>> Yeah.
>> Really?
>> I'm serious about it, yeah.
>> Today at the challenge, Katie
chose to throw me into the water
rather than Gregg, and I said,
"Wow, that's interesting.
If Katie is willing to sell me
out for a night on the yacht,
there's no way she's going to
hold on to me for a million
dollars."
We have a couple choices to
make.
>> Okay, go.
>> The way that I see it right
now, we have lost control of
the game.
>> Why?
>> We're not making the
decisions.
Gregg and Jenn are.
>> Why, 'cause they won one
challenge?
>> No, uh-uh.
I think that they got Katie, and
one of the three of us out.
Me, Tom, you.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I think it goes in that
order.
I know they're ready to turn
on you.
I know for a fact.
>> And you think Katie is in
with that?
>> Yeah, I think she is.
>> Caryn warned me that Katie
was looking to get rid of me,
but I still wasn't willing to
take her word over Katie's at
that point.
Now, Ian says Katie, she's now
become the shady lady Katie,
looking to dump us and go into
the final with Gregg and Jenn.
>> I think Gregg is a dark horse
right now.
>> Yeah.
>> Nobody would vote against him
in the final two.
>> Nobody. Especially...
>> Why?
>> He's never made any enemies.
>> He hasn't pissed anybody off,
he's very affable.
He works hard.
>> What do you think?
>> We go for Gregg tomorrow
night.
>> Do we?
>> We'd tie, wouldn't we?
>> Yeah.
Three would go against me,
and three would go against
Gregg.
What more do you propose?
>> I don't know what the next
step is.
>> Suddenly, the sequence of
events have fallen into place
that have really benefited me.
Those five had an alliance,
and, lucky for me, that alliance
is breaking down now.
I'm not sure exactly what's
going to happen.
The only thing I can do is
to keep close to Tom and Ian.
That's all I can do.
That's my only hope.
>> Gregg, you got to go on
first.
>> This is awesome.
>> Oh, my God.
>> We get to the boat and
Captain Mike greets us and lets
us know this is a day of being
pampered, VIP treatment.
>> Rooms one and two.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> He shows us to the bunks and
when we walked in we found
our bathing suits which we
haven't seen since we left
for the island.
(shouting)
We were so excited to get on
to the next event.
So we quickly scrubbed up, threw
the bathrobe on and then we went
up to the deck for full-body
massages.
It felt like finally I was on
vacation in Palau.
(whispers indistinctly)
That feels great.
This is unbelievable.
I'm sitting there loving it,
just relaxing, and then I
noticed the hands feel a little
colder, feel a little different.
Next thing I know I get a hard
smack on the ass, and I do a
double take.
My eyes have been closed,
I've been daydreaming.
And my best friend from home,
Greg, is staring at me, and he's
like what's up?
>> Looking fine, dude.
>> Doing well, man.
>> Yeah, hell, yeah.
>> We were both in disbelief.
>> It was nuts.
We didn't know how to react.
>> Cheers.
>> I don't even know where
to begin.
>> Cheers.
>> Oh, my God, what's this?
What?!
Oh, my God.
>> Shrimp and...
>> What is this?
>> Dig in, man.
>> This is an onion ring.
>> This is beautiful.
>> Calamari.
>> This is, by far, the best
reward challenge,
I mean, obviously.
>> Oh, my God!
>> You got... you got all the
stuff?
>> All of a sudden, I get a tap
on my shoulder, and it's my
sister Kim.
All I could do was bawl, like
cry.
That's all I could do.
I was just like, oh, my God.
She's here!
>> We're going to have a party!
>> Stan is my sister's husband.
He is the brother I never had.
My sister just had a baby,
so she wasn't able to come,
so it was the next-best thing
to having my sister.
I couldn't ask for a better
reward.
>> It was the most phenomenal
experience of my lifetime.
>> Now they're doing it.
>> But you're sure that she's
ready to go against me with
them?
>> Yep.
>> Mm-hmm, I know that.
>> So Gregg should go tomorrow?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> It would be very easy
in a tie situation.
You put Gregg and Caryn up
against the wall.
>> And so we need to break this
tie.
>> Katie is forced to switch
her vote, because she knows that
if she doesn't, she has to pick
a rock.
>> Right.
>> The way the rules are, if
there is a tie at Tribal
Council, both members who were
voted on, those two will become
safe and it comes down to the
rest of us, reaching in a bag,
pulling out a colored stone.
Whoever gets the purple stone
is going home that night.
That's a calculated risk
on our part.
>> Maybe she picks the rock and
then we have to pick a rock
to see who goes home.
It sucks, but I can go to Tribal
Council willing to take the
rock, you know what I mean?
Like, I'm willing to make
that gamble.
I came to play a game.
>> That's the plan.
>> You and I are both willing
to choose rocks.
>> And we should be.
>> That's right.
Let's do this.
>> Desperate times call for
desperate measures, right?
>> We have a plan.
>> Tom and I have decided that
we're going to force a tie
at Tribal Council.
We've prepared ourselves for the
idea that we might be going
home, but this is a risk we
had to take.
>> It's a gamble.
Hopefully, Katie realizes that
she doesn't want to pick a rock.
She wants to stay in the game.
This is the biggest step that
you and I have to get to the
final three.
That's why it's important that
he does not see it coming.
Any leaks and we're done.
The game's over for us.
It's a delicate operation that
needs to be handled with the
utmost of care.
It's kind of like taking a bag
of potato chips from a fat man.
You can do it, but you'd better
do it quick.
Otherwise, he'll turn around
and sit on you.
>> You've been acting the last
two days like you're about to
be sent home.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Continue to act that way.
>> Okay.
>> Do not say a word...
> Don't be chipper.
Be down and dour.
>> Okay.
>> Okay?
>> Yep.
I can do it.
I'm psyched.
I'm totally psyched.
This is really working out well.
I think we can pull this off,
I really do.
Because you know what?
I'm a very good actress,
very, very good.
>> This is so gorgeous.
We're on a boat going to this
lagoon.
We're just thinking snorkeling,
we have no idea.
>> I don't know.
>> Oh, my gosh, there's
dolphins!
>> All of a sudden, all of us
see these fins that are just
swimming through the water and
we're like oh, my God, no way,
no way!
>> Hi.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Swimming with the dolphins
was, by far, the most magical
moment I've ever had.
It was something I've always
wanted to do.
I mean, it's like my dream.
>> Hi!
>> Oh, this is...
>> Oh!
>> I'm so happy.
>> It was the most surreal
experience I've ever had,
and to be able to share that
with my sister was just
incredible.
I kept going, "I can't believe
you're here for this."
It's just the experience of
a lifetime, and she got to
share it with me.
I never wanted it to end.
It was unbelievable.
>> Cheers. I can't reach.
>> After the day of snorkeling,
and hanging with the dolphins,
we were able to do a little
strategy talk.
This was our opportunity
to confirm that, hey, guys,
it's us three to the final
three.
We happen to have a good bond,
and it just also benefits
the three of us to go to
the final three.
>> I came into this knowing that
I might have to jump ship, if
it comes down to it.
My strategy is to stick with
those people that make the
decisions until those people no
longer have any power, and then
jump to the next person that
makes the decision.
>> Yeah.
>> We all realize the threats
that Ian and Tom are, so it was
good to get agreement with that.
It felt real.
It felt true.
And I believe that that bond
is-is tight till the end.
>> I hear a boat.
>> I think it's them.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Here we go, guys.
>> Let's do this right.
>> I'm sour and dour.
>> Hey, hey!
>> What's happening?
>> Who's that?
>> I don't know.
>> That's their families.
>> Oh, no.
>> Those are your families.
Today I think my worst fears
were, uh... realized.
Only three family members got
to spend time with their loved
ones, and the other three are
left on the beach to, uh, hear
the stories.
>> How you doing? I'm Tom.
>> This one cuts and twists,
and, uh, it's tough.
>> We're almost there.
>> I know.
>> We'll plow through.
>> Yeah.
>> Get-Get this thing done.
>> It'll get tough, you know,
when you guys get down to
picking people that you care
about off.
>> Sure.
>> Well, if there's one person
that, uh...
>> You've got somebody looking
out for her out here, it's me
looking out for her, so...
>> Good.
I appreciate that.
>> When my friend Greg had to
leave, it was just really tough.
>> Remember, we're all proud
of you at home.
>> You know, it was only a year
ago that my dad passed away,
and the grieving still happens
every day.
Just tell my mom that I love
her so much and I cannot wait
to just spend time with her
when I get back.
Will you tell her that?
>> I will.
>> Just tell her...
>> This might have been the last
love fest in camp.
>> Let's do a really cheesy...
(indistinct voices)
>> Now it's time to get control
of the game again, and focus on
the coming six days and what
needs to be accomplished.
It has been a good run, but it's
about to get a little rough.
That little trip that they took
may cost them big.
>> Tree mail.
>> What have we got?
>> "Some played hard, some
just watched and others just
skated by.
To make your chances one
in five, give this one your
best try.
"Usually this is a second
chance, but for some it's
all brand new.
So embrace the challenges of
the past, or tonight you could
be through."
>> What?
>> Wow.
>> In order for our plan to
work, a lot has to happen today.
Worst case scenario is Gregg
wins immunity, so we really
need to work hard today and
make sure that doesn't happen.
I didn't come to play for sixth
or fifth or fourth or third or
second.
I'm going to do my damndest
to make sure that I come across
the finish line first.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How's it going, everybody?
>> Hey, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Ready to get to
today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Ian... give it up.
Immunity once again back up
for grabs.
It is rare in this game
of Survivor that you get
a second chance.
Today's challenge provides just
that-- a second chance to
revisit some of the challenges
from the past.
It is a Survivor
elimination-style challenge.
All six of you will
race up the net maze.
The first five to finish will
move on to the next round, where
you will race to a symbol-- a
land version of the sea star
puzzle.
The first four to finish that
will move on to the next round,
where you will eat three balut,
a partially-developed duck egg.
The first three to get the balut
down the quickest move on to the
next round, where you will race
to untie a box, retrieve a flag,
string it up the flag pole.
The first two to finish that
move on to the last round.
The last two Survivors will
compete in a head-to-head
shooting competition.
The first Survivor to knock
out their three targets wins
immunity.
Take your spots, get started.
All right, for immunity, first
five to finish move on to the
next round.
Survivors, ready.
Go!
Tom and Ian and Gregg up first.
Tom and Gregg neck and neck.
Ian right behind.
Jenn in it.
Tom is across.
Gregg's down, moving on.
Ian's moving on.
Jenn's moving on to the next
round.
Down to Katie and Caryn.
Katie moves on to the next
round.
Caryn, you're out.
Have a seat on the stump.
Moving on to the next round.
This is what you're trying to
solve.
First four to finish their sea
star puzzle move on to the next
round.
Survivors, ready.
Go.
Everybody making some good
progress.
Gregg has the bottom row.
Ian has the bottom two rows.
Gregg getting closer.
Uh, Jeff, I think I'm done.
Ian has it.
Take a spot on the mat.
Tom has it.
He's moving on.
Take a spot on the mat with Ian.
Tom and Ian moving on.
Looking for two more to join
them.
>> Okay. There we go.
>> PROBST: Gregg has it.
He's moving on to the next
round.
It's down to Jenn and Katie--
one person moving on,
one person sitting down.
>> Wait, I got it.
>> PROBST: Jenn has it.
Jenn moving on.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Katie, you're out.
Take a seat with Caryn.
>> Damn it!
>> Jenn, Gregg, Ian, Tom,
moving on.
Reveal the balut.
The first three people to get
their balut down the quickest
move on to the next round.
Survivors, ready.
Go.
Ian shoving them in as fast
as he can.
Jenn staying with the guys.
Ian has all three in his mouth.
Tom has all three in his mouth.
Gregg and Jenn bringing up the
rear.
Tom's good, and moving on.
Ian's good, and moving on.
It's down to Jenn and Gregg.
First one to finish moves on.
Jenn puts the third balut
in her mouth.
Gregg has all three in his
mouth.
Jenn very close.
Jenn moving on to the next
round.
Gregg is out.
First two to untie their box,
get the flag out, clip it in
and string their flag up
to the top of the pole move
on to the final round.
Survivors, ready.
Go.
Ian using his mouth.
Jenn making quick work
of the knots.
Ian and Tom very tight.
Got to get your flag out
and up the flag pole.
Keep moving, Jenn.
You're falling behind.
Ian has his flag.
Tom has his flag.
Tom's clipped in.
Tom to the top, moving on.
Ian moving on.
>> Damn it.
> PROBST: Jenn is out.
Join the others.
All right, moving on
to the last round.
Ian, you're up first.
First person to knock out
three targets wins immunity.
>> I'll go with blue.
>> PROBST: Ian takes his aim.
Ian connects with his first
target.
He's up one-oh.
Tom looking to even the score.
Tom misses.
Ian leads one-oh.
Ian looking to extend the lead.
And he does.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Ian drills his second
target.
Tom needs to get on the board.
Tom nicks it, doesn't break it.
Tom, still not on the board.
All Ian has to do is knock
out his last blue target.
And he does.
>> Whoo!
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Ian wins immunity.
>> Nice job. Good shooting.
>> PROBST: Ian, get over here.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Nicely done.
>> Thanks.
> PROBST: Back-to-back
challenges, safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
Tom, Jenn, Gregg, Katie, Caryn,
not the same for you.
One of you is going home
tonight.
Should be a fun afternoon
back at camp.
I'll see you at Tribal Council
tonight.
Head on back.
>> I remember the jungle course
being a lot easier on day three.
(Jenn laughing)
>> Ian won immunity for tonight.
That darn gun, man, that is my
Achilles heel.
It's very fortunate I became a
fireman rather than a cop,
because it would just be
dangerous for everybody.
Well, that's okay.
'Cause you know what?
I was going five, you were going
four, so rightfully so, I should
be the one taking the risk.
We've got a plan in place.
Ian and I are gonna pretend that
there's nothing going on,
everything is fine.
But the three of us--
myself, Ian and Caryn--
will vote for Gregg tonight,
the other three will vote
for Caryn, and then we'll
go to a draw and be forced
to pick a stone.
But it won't be Ian who has
to choose-- he won immunity.
It'll be me.
So I'm very vulnerable, but it's
better to play it hard and go
home tonight than to sit around
here and just wait to be
eliminated by their threesome.
>> So, we're good with the
immunity today.
We needed Caryn not to get it.
>> Yeah. We should all be pretty
proud of the fact we looked
around and said, "Hey, five
of us."
>> Right.
>> Yeah.
>> We're there.
I was a little nervous
stepping away from the game for
a while, so it was comforting
to come back and get no
mysterious looks or no...
people trying to connive.
So, I can say with a lot of
confidence that Caryn will be
going home tonight.
I mean, you could tell, she's
just out of commission today.
>> Caryn's in a Janu place, huh?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, that's what happens
when you know you're done.
>> Caryn is winning an Academy
Award right now.
She is lying in the hut, down
and sour, like she thinks she's
going home.
Perfect. Just the way
we told her to.
So, this should be a total
surprise tonight.
>> I think so.
>> Interesting or...
>> No. Just it's gonna be...
>> It's always interesting.
>> Yeah.
>> I'll start getting some
firewood.
>> All right.
>> I just feel so rejuvenated.
>> Yeah.
>> We have a good advantage.
The next one, though, is the
big one.
>> It's big, yeah.
>> Yeah.
Oh, exactly.
>> Things going okay?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Good. Good.
>> I was just thinking today
a lot about family, and I just
wanted to talk to you about it.
I told Stan right before he
left, uh, I was gonna watch
over you.
>> Aw...
>> And that I was gonna
protect you.
>> That's still the deal for me.
>> Good.
>> There's only two people in
this game that I've made
promises to; Tom's one, Katie's
the other-- I told Katie I
wouldn't write her name down,
and I told her brother-in-law
I had her back, and that means
a lot to me, so...
I'm gonna stay true to that.
What I wanted to talk to you
about was, we're gonna flip
it tonight.
>> Yeah.
>> What do you mean?
>> Um, Caryn and Tom, um, and I
are gonna vote for Gregg.
>> Yeah.
>> What?!
>> Yeah, we're flipping the game
around.
We're gonna force a tie, unless
you vote Gregg.
>> If it's a tie, then what
happens?
>> It goes to rocks.
You know, that's why I wanted to
give you the heads-up.
>> Ian pulled me aside, like,
right before we went to Tribal
Council with the idea of taking
out Gregg.
I had some issues with it.
I'm, like, you know it's really
unfair for you just to come in
and say, this is what we're
doing, this is what the plan is.
Think about it-- for you and
Tom, that's great.
But I'm just thinking as
far as I'm concerned, I was
in a good place.
>> I know that you're playing
the game, and I know that you
don't want to take me to the
finals because you're afraid...
>> 'Cause I wouldn't win, Ian.
>> Katie, if you and I go up
against each other, it's gonna
be a lot closer than you think.
>> That's such crap.
>> He's, like, "Do I have a
reason to feel paranoid?"
I'm, like, I don't think so.
>> No. I mean, that goes without
saying, right?
>> I just don't want you to get
dumped.
I'd rather see you in the final
two with me.
>> Right.
The reason Ian wants me with him
in the end is so he'll win.
Tom wants the same thing.
>> I'm ready to go.
>> When it comes down to it,
I'm gonna have to make a
decision so I can have a
better chance of winning.
I'm here to win a million
dollars just like anyone else.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury.
Coby, Janu...
and Steph, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Let's talk about the reward
challenge.
This late in the game, they can
be good news/bad news.
You don't want to be away from
camp and miss the politics.
On the other hand, if you don't
win, you might miss out on
something fantastic, like a
surprise visit from the loved
ones.
Gregg, did it turn out to be
a good thing?
>> Yeah, it turned out
to be a great experience.
But on the other side of the
coin, it-it did hurt to know
that I was leaving behind
three tribe members, and they
didn't get to share in the
opportunity, so, you know, it's
a tough situation to be in.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
the reward challenge itself.
It is designed to bring out
the status of a tribe.
Caryn, you were first out.
Yeah, that was very hard.
>> For some reason, they felt
I had too many rewards.
And I didn't feel I had won that
much, but, you know, there was
obviously some resentment about
that, 'cause my torch went out
like that.
>> PROBST: Do you think that's
all it was, you had a little
more food, nothing else?
>> I do think so.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: How can it not have
more implications than just food
when you watch Gregg ask Jenn
for permission about what to do?
(laughter)
You guys are laughing;
I'm serious.
We're down to the nitty-gritty
here for a million bucks.
Jenn, you're clearly seen as
somewhat of a couple with Gregg.
Are you at all worried that
that's going to hurt you at some
point in this big, happy family?
>> I do worry about that
a little bit.
Um, but I do think that we're
both playing a very individual
game.
>> I think people know that Jenn
and I do have a bond and a
relationship, and, you know, it
wasn't malicious or even
strategic for me to want to
spend some time with her.
But that's not gonna have people
turn against each other or, you
know, change your strategy for
just one day away.
>> PROBST: Caryn, back to you.
You were first out.
You brought more than anybody
tonight.
It looks like you brought
everything you have.
>> I've been carrying my stuff
to every Tribal Council.
Janu, Willard, Coby and I were
not part of the five-person
alliance.
So...
I always feel vulnerable.
>> PROBST: Tom, it's now down
to six people who have been
together from day one.
Has it changed how you think
about voting somebody out?
Because you're gonna hurt
somebody.
Somebody's going home tonight,
and they're moving right over
there.
>> Right.
We are friends, and we are
looking to slit each other's
throats at night.
I think that right now you do
have an "all is fair in love
and war" attitude that's all
about advancing your move
down the board.
>> PROBST: All right, Ian,
once again, you have the
immunity necklace.
It is yours to keep or give up
to somebody else.
>> Um, I think I'll hold
on to it tonight.
>> PROBST: With that, it is time
to vote.
Tom, you're up.
>> Gregg, you're the dark horse.
And it's just time for the
dark horse to ride off into
the sunset.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final-- person voted
out will be asked to leave the
Tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Caryn.
Caryn. Two votes Caryn.
Gregg. Two votes Caryn,
one vote Gregg.
two votes Gregg.
Gregg. That's three votes Gregg,
two votes Caryn.
I'll read the last vote.
13th person voted out
of Survivor: Palau and the
fourth member of our jury...
Gregg.
>> You guys are good.
>> PROBST: You need to bring me
your torch.
Gregg, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, the message seems clear--
with six days left, nobody's
safe anymore.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on...
Survivor.
>> I don't really have a deal
with Tom.
>> We know you have a deal with
Tom.
>> PROBST: The women compare
notes.
>> Katie just cleaned house.
>> PROBST: And Ian and Katie
have a blow-out.
>> You said you would never
lie to me, and you did.
>> Damn!
>> You didn't even think about
how that was gonna make me feel
to have you go against your
word.
>> You want me to step out?
I mean, I'll do it. I'll do it.
>> I think I'd be lying if I
said I wasn't completely
surprised.
My hat's off to 'em, though.
They got me, they got me good.
Um, I learned a lot of things.
An experience is nothing unless
you share it with other people
who you love.
Jenn, best of luck.
I appreciate your friendship
out on the island, and, uh, look
forward to... hanging out soon.