>> JEFF PROBST: We are cruising
through a remote and absolutely
breathtaking section of the
Pacific.
Crystal-clear water that is home
to one of the most spectacular
natural wonders of the world,
the island paradise of Palau.
It is a unique landscape,
featuring hundreds
of lush islands,
magnificent coral reefs
and an underwater sanctuary
of sea life like no other.
♪ ♪
Sharks, manta rays,
giant clams, and literally
millions of jellyfish.
But this paradise has
an infamous history.
These waters were home to some
of the most fierce battles
of World War II,
and the remnants of war
haunt these jungles
and litter the ocean floor
in a watery grave.
It is an eerie mix
of man's explosive past
and nature's power to reclaim.
For the first time ever,
there are 20 survivors.
They've been set adrift with
only the clothes on their backs
and one canteen of water each.
Everything they've come to
expect about the way this game
begins will soon be wiped out.
39 days, 20 people,
one survivor.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
Welcome... to Survivor: Palau.
Just behind you, that beach
is your new home.
Waiting for you,
you will find:
two machetes,
one map to water,
along with the most valuable
thing in this game: immunity.
There are two
immunity necklaces.
One for the first woman,
one for the first man
who can get to shore
and claim them.
How you get to shore is up to
you.
You're still about a mile out.
You can paddle in,
you can start swimming,
a little of both.
You are all on your own,
it is your choice,
but I suggest you make
a decision and start acting now,
because this game is on.
>> Paddle.
>> Let's paddle.
Paddle.
>> PROBST: Good luck.
>> Jeff's a son of a bitch.
I can tell you that.
Hell, I thought
we were gonna get, you know,
some breakfast,
food and water or something.
Hell, no.
I knew he was gonna say
something like that,
that he was gonna say,
"The game is on."
Something told me.
We was...
pretty much in trouble.
>> As we were rowing the boat,
and we were getting
closer and closer to the beach,
everybody was thinking,
"Should I jump out?
"Should I swim to the shore?
Should I try to beat the boat?"
>> ( grunts )
>> The fight was on immediately.
And then people said,
"Oh, I'll take your spot
rowing in the back."
And other people were
whispering and wondering,
oh, is that because they want
to be at the back of the boat
so that when the boat gets close
to shore, they can run off?
>> As we were slowly rowing in,
I was, like,
I think it's close enough,
I'm gonna jump, I'm gonna swim.
'Cause I'm a pretty good
swimmer, so I figured
I could beat the boat.
Didn't seem like we were moving.
Everybody, I'm going.
>> Stephenie just said,
"I can't take it.
I'm gonna jump in,"
and then I...
of course,
I was right behind her.
I'm out of here.
All right, let's go!
>> Watch out for the oar!
>> I got in,
and, like, every two strokes,
there went the boat,
and I was, like, "Oh, my God,
that's the dumbest thing
I've ever done."
If we get off,
can we get back on?
What are your names again?
( others laughing )
Oh, my God!
Bad idea, I guess?
>> When Stephenie and Jonathan
dove in the water,
everyone's, like... (sputters)
(laughs) "You don't want to be
the first one to dive in!"
God!
That is a gigantic target
on your head.
>> We were all excited,
because we wanted to jump
and start swimming,
but we didn't.
We kept waiting and waiting
and waiting.
>> The competitive nature
in me was like, "You got to take
off your shoes and go!"
( whooping )
>> Good job!
I got the immunity necklace.
I was not gonna let that...
little young girl beat me.
>> Whoo!
>> Good job.
Nice to meet you.
What was your name again?
>> Jeff.
>> Ian.
>> Good job, man.
>> Ian, he was the first one
up there.
Get his ass up there,
skinny boy, I'm telling you,
that's a fast little booger.
Well, I don't even know
if we have a tribe,
because I noticed
the banner just says,
"SURVIVOR: Palau."
It doesn't have
any tribe name on it.
>> One map, we're all together.
>> Because you've never seen
the game start this way, with
20 people, you get a little...
I found myself getting
a little paranoid.
You know, we're not a tribe,
we don't have our buffs,
we're just getting to know
everyone's name.
>> I'm Jolanda.
"Jo" if you can't say it.
>> Oh, you guys, they're out
there!
>> Something's gonna happen,
something big's gonna happen.
We can't just remain
as a group of 20.
It's a big question mark.
We don't have a clue
>> All right, everybody,
let's, um...
think about who wants to do
water, who wants to do shelter.
>> I'll do shelter.
>> I'll do water.
>> Okay, water people...
>> Water.
>> So we got one,
two, three, four,
and Coby's five.
Okay. That sound
like a good plan?
>> Say what?
>> Five people go look for water
and 15 start
on the shelter?
>> Yeah.
>> When we got on the beach,
it was such a bore
with all the immunities
and just the craziness
of just being dropped off.
But, actually, I think we got
to things fairly quickly.
I mean, we found the map
to the water source,
we started thinking
about shelter and food,
and so people just broke off,
a group of four
broke off to go get water.
And then everybody else
stayed with shelter.
I mean, it was very quick,
it happened very fast.
>> He knocked it down
like Paul Bunyan.
>> I know. ( laughs )
>> You okay?
>> Yeah.
>> You know, it was funny,
I mean, uh,
everybody's just walking around
in different directions.
"Let's get the water,"
"Let's build a shelter."
And, uh,
you just got to watch that.
You know, I had a few people
try to wrangle me
into doing the fire,
and I'm just, like,
that's a loser job, man.
All right.
>> Let's get this going.
>> Oh.
I got to go
to the bathroom.
>> I'll get some more sticks.
>> Do we have a strong man here?
Come on.
Are you like Hercules?
Come on, Hercules.
Hercules! Hercules! Hercules!
We came out
in the clothes we had on,
and were kind of taken by
surprise that we couldn't have,
you know, the clothes that we
had thought we were gonna have
with us.
It was really difficult,
I know, for a lot of people.
But there have been some great
modifications to it, so...
>> Don't, like, hack,
like, saw.
>> Oh, yeah.
Oh, I've made shorts
back in the day.
>> Oh, gosh, they're just
chopping things off left and
right, pants are falling off,
and skirts are getting
a little bit higher,
and shirts are getting tied up.
I had mine tied up earlier,
but... decided to...
stop for now.
>> I'm trying to find
the middle.
>> What's that?
>> That big rocky thing.
( whooping )
We found it!
Yes!
( whooping )
What else?
>> We were so excited
to get to the water.
>> Coby!
>> What the hell is this?
>> Shoes!
So we finally
found the water source,
and also found a bag
of everybody's shoes,
which was really nice
to take back into camp,
Like, "Look, no more stilettos.
We have real shoes."
>> We can't let young,
good-looking people
have all the power.
>> That's what I was thinking.
>> 'Cause there's a lot of them.
>> Yeah.
Me and Coby pretty much knew
when we saw each other
that we were going to be, you
know, kindred to one another
'cause we understood
being different,
we understood being ostracized.
Yeah, I have to say,
I sighed a sigh of relief
when I saw you 'cause I realized
I wasn't gonna be the weirdest
one here.
>> ( laughing )
>> I mean that in a loving way.
>> I felt the same way.
I was, like, "Oh, we're
gonna totally get along."
>> You can tell that Angie and I
are both cut from the same
cloth, in that we think we're
different and we're the
outcasts, but I think we're both
gonna have to watch it
when it comes
to the context of the game,
'cause if we're
too much of an outcast,
obviously it's gonna
make us a target.
>> Now how do we get
that up there?
I don't know.
Tom, what were
you thinking with this?
I got this up here.
Actually, what we're gonna need
is, we're gonna need somebody
to get up here
to start putting
these cross pieces.
>> The boys really
got together and they used...
We used one big tree
as our base for our shelter,
and then they put reeds up,
and they said we needed
to tie them at the top,
so I offered.
>> Oh, my God.
Nice job.
>> Oh, watch it.
>> There you go.
I'm loving you already.
>> Okay.
I don't know if it was
a good thing or bad thing,
but I wanted to help
and I figured
my rock-climbing skills
would help,
so I climbed that had puppy like
a monkey and I did what I could.
>> Come on, sucker.
>> Where's the sun?
Beating down on me
all day long.
I think it is, like, 2:30.
Do you believe this?
>> I know.
It's amazing.
>> So what are you thinking?
Ian, me, you?
Just an early something here?
We might all be
split tomorrow, but, uh....
>> I'm in with that,
with you guys,
'cause we would be strong.
The whole thing could
be reshuffled, but...
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> Grasshoppers have protein.
( yelling ):
Wow!
I just ate my first grasshopper!
Oh, my God.
Do you want to knock off
threats, or do you want to...
You don't know how the game's
going to play out
after that, right?
>> Are you not leaning
towards any of the girls?
>> Honestly, I'm not leaning
towards anyone.
>> I'm leaning towards Jonathan.
The one who jumped in the water.
>> Although he worked so hard
today...
>> Everybody's working hard,
really, when you look at it now,
I mean, in their own way.
I'm just going
with connections.
I don't real connect with him.
I don't think I've
said anything to him
the whole time
I've been here. Honestly.
I don't think
he's talked to me either.
Everybody's assumption
at this point
is that we're all
basically screwed
because we all think we have
Tribal Council, like, now.
>> We don't even know if we're
going to be on the same team.
>> I know, but that's why you
just got to go for today.
Right, but that
could change tomorrow.
>> So we thought we had three
days of at least getting
to know everybody, at least.
You know, we don't know
if we have that,
so everybody's security
has been blown,
so everybody's freaking out.
>> Whoa!
>> But I've definitely
gone to different groups
all day today and said, "Who
are you going to vote for?
"Really? That's interesting.
"What about voting
for this person?
What about Jonathan?
Hmm. Good."
And as long as I do it subtly...
You go, boy.
...and sneak it in there,
you can change their minds,
'cause at this point, everybody
doesn't want it to be them.
Good morning, everybody.
>> Good morning.
>> This one's cashed.
>> PROBST: What's going on,
guys?
>> Oh, hey, how you
doing there, Jeff?
>> PROBST: What's up?
>> Here we go.
>> We got visitors!
>> PROBST: What's up?
>> Whoo, Jeff.
>> PROBST: How are you?
How's everybody doing?
Big group.
Anxious to know
what's happening?
>> ALL: Yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, so
Jolanda and Ian,
you guys were the first
two to the beach.
Who was the first person?
>> Ian.
>> PROBST: Ian.
All right, Ian,
take a spot right over here,
Jolanda right over here.
Getting a little
uncomfortable over here?
>> Yep.
>> A little nervous now.
>> PROBST: How's that immunity
feel, Jolanda?
>> It feels good.
>> PROBST: It ought to feel
real good.
The immunity necklaces
that you're wearing
guarantee that you're gonna
stay in this game
for at least ten more minutes.
Which cannot be said
for the other 18 of you.
We're gonna divide
into two tribes
with nine members each,
that's 18 people.
There are 20 of you.
Two people will not be selected
to be on a tribe.
Two people will get on a boat,
immediately, and be sent home.
Ian and Jolanda you will make
the first picks, alternating
between men and women.
Each time you choose a person,
that person will choose the
next member of the tribe.
Ian, because were you first to
the beach, you will select
first; you're picking a girl.
>> Okay.
>> Uh, Katie.
>> PROBST: Jolanda,
you're picking a guy.
>> Bobby Jon.
>> Good choice.
>> PROBST: So, Ian and Jolanda,
your work is done.
The person you pick
will now pick.
Katie, you're picking a guy.
>> Tom.
>> PROBST: Bobby.
>> Stephenie.
>> PROBST: Tom, you're picking
a woman.
>> I'm gonna take Janu.
>> PROBST: Janu, still in the
game and relieved.
Steph, you're picking a guy.
>> Jeff.
>> PROBST: Jeff, gonna make it
to at least the first challenge.
Janu, you're picking a man.
>> Gregg.
>> PROBST: Janu, you look upset.
>> No, it's just kind of weird.
>> PROBST: Kind of weird?
You don't do this a lot?
Jeff, you're picking a girl.
>> Kim.
>> PROBST: Kim stays in the
game.
Gregg, you're picking a woman.
>> Jenn.
>> PROBST: Kim, you're picking
a guy.
>> James.
>> PROBST: Jenn, you're picking
a guy, tough decision.
Getting down to it.
>> Uh...
Coby.
>> PROBST: James.
>> Ashlee.
>> PROBST: Coby, you're
picking a woman.
>> Caryn.
>> PROBST: Caryn, how does that
feel to be standing over there?
What's going
through your head?
It's not a good
feeling, Jeff.
It's better to be on this side.
>> PROBST: Ashlee,
you're picking a guy.
>> Ibrehem.
>> PROBST: You each have one
pick left.
You're gonna pick one guy,
gonna pick one girl.
In doing so, you're gonna pick
the final members of your tribe
and effectively vote out
two people from this game.
How you feeling, Wanda?
>> It's been an awful long time
since my heart pounded this
fast.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, how you
feeling?
>> I'm just...
My heart's beating.
I thought I was gonna
be picked before this.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
make the final selections.
Caryn, you're picking a guy.
Make your decision.
>> Willard.
>> PROBST: Willard stays in the
game, Jonathan is out of the
game.
Ibrehem, you're picking a woman.
Make your decision.
>> Angie.
>> PROBST: Angie stays in the
game.
Wanda is out of the game.
Tough to say, but, guys,
it is time for you to go.
Right past me, you got a boat
waiting out here.
>> Go have some chips and
salsa.
>> Go get it, Wanda.
Go get it, John.
Come on, now.
>> I love you, too.
Have a good one, guys.
>> Bye!
>> I was really, really,
really sad.
But that's all right.
I'm gonna wipe my tears
and refocus.
That's in the past.
It's a whole new game.
All right.
Let's hand out the buffs.
( cheering )
>> All right.
>> PROBST: You guys are Ulong.
You wear blue.
Your tribe-- Karor.
You will wear brown.
Brown.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Okay, so you're now
two tribes-- Ulong, Karor.
Two tribes still living
together on the same beach.
Head on back.
>> Get out of here.
>> Are you serious?
( laughing )
>> That's the plan.
>> I really thought you're
giving away the competition.
( laughing )
>> It's definitely going
to be weird,
all staying on one beach
together, though.
It's still coming through,
though.
>> It hurts to be last, but...
>> Oh, yeah.
I felt horrible
being picked last.
I didn't think that I was going
to be picked last.
>> How many girls we have, five?
>> I thought 100% that Coby
was going to pick me.
>> Five and four.
I don't feel like I'm on the
tribe that I should be on,
so there's no kindred feelings
with my tribe.
I'm the odd man out.
>> Never had anything
against you, ever.
>> Guys, if there's any sort
of competition
that they are trying to put
into this game already,
let's not be the ones
that start into that.
>> No, no, no.
>> Our average age is higher.
but let's try to weaken them
when it comes to physical stuff.
>> I'm altogether
very, very happy.
I wanted a wise tribe, if I had
the opportunity to pick.
We got a little bit of the
older folks, which I really
like, and we're up against a
bunch of the young bucks.
You compare the tribes and you
see a definite difference.
They come to you
and say, oh, listen,
so and so on your team
was talking about you...
they are just trying
to break us up.
>> I love everybody
on this team.
>> We definitely have
some kind of advantage,
which I don't care
what you say, you know,
smart's in it, too, but
athletics is going to play
a part in it, also.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
You guys ready to get
to the challenge?
>> ALL: Yeah.
>> PROBST: It is both reward
and immunity.
Here's how it works.
Both tribes are going
to compete head-to-head
in a jungle obstacle course.
You'll make your way
through a net maze
and then through
a series of tires.
You'll reach a covered supply
dump, where you will find
a set of paddles
you must take tied
to four survival items
you can choose
to take or leave behind.
Fire in the form of flint,
two cans to carry water,
flour and rice for your food
and a tarp for shelter,
but the crates
that these items are in
have been weighted to make them
very heavy to carry.
Untie all of your items,
continue through the course
carrying the items.
You'll go up and over a wall,
through a jungle swamp.
When you reach your canoe,
drop the items you chose
to take with you,
get in the canoe,
paddle out to retrieve a flag
and race back to shore.
The first tribe
to get back to their mat
with all nine tribe members
and their tribe-colored flag
wins immunity and all the items
they carried to that mat,
keeping in mind you can only win
the items that make it
all the way to the finish.
So, it becomes a choice.
You want to win
to guarantee yourself immunity,
but you want to win
with as many items as possible.
Now let's get to immunity.
Ian, Jolanda,
you can you take those off.
Like I said, those guaranteed
you'd stay in the game
ten more minutes.
Those ten minutes are over.
This is what you covet now.
Immunity-- the only thing
that keeps you safe in this game
is this.
As long as you have it,
you can't be voted out.
Take your spots
and wait for my go.
Here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors, ready...
Go!
Tom with a big head start.
Neck and neck right now.
Tom the first one over
for Koror,
followed by Gregg.
Here comes Jeff for Ulong.
>> Come on, come on, come on!
>> PROBST: There's Ian for
Koror.
We're tight.
There's Jenn.
Koror got a bit of a lead.
Here comes Caryn for Ulong.
Ulong in one fell swoop
catches up.
>> Come on, let's go, guys!
>> PROBST: Ulong moving on.
Koror, go!
Up and over, however you want.
Neck and neck still.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Start pulling those
off.
You gotta move all your items
to the mat before you can
start untying them.
>> Let's go, guys.
>> PROBST: Get that last item,
Koror.
Ulong, start untying.
This is where you
make your first decision.
Are you going to take
all your items or not.
Koror working together well.
Koror, very close.
Koror is free.
Koror is leaving
their food and their water,
taking only their fire
with them.
>> You guys, come on!
We gotta go.
>> We're gonna lose.
>> I'm telling you,
I think we should go.
You guys, finish it up.
We gotta go.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Ulong, keep it
moving.
Koror first to the wall.
>> Two people push me
up that wall.
One, two, three.
>> Come on!
>> This way, this way.
You got it, Ulong!
>> Get out of the way.
Ahh!
No...
>> Try jumping down.
>> PROBST: Here comes Ulong
right on your tail.
Koror having trouble
getting Willard over.
Ulong brought food
and water, did not bring fire.
Interesting strategy.
Koror is up and over.
Koror, go.
Ulong really struggling.
Koror making their way
through the swamp
with a big lead.
( grunts and groans )
Ulong finally over the wall.
Koror first to their canoe.
The strategy was
to only bring fire,
and it's working so far.
Paddle out.
Get your flag.
Come on.
>> PROBST:
Let's go, Ulong!
Keep it moving.
You're still in this.
Get in, get in.
The rest up front.
Ulong, go.
Paddle out.
Hustle up, guys.
Good paddlers might
be able to catch them.
>> Get to that side.
Right side paddle backwards.
>> To the right side!
>> Paddle faster.
>> Paddle on the right.
>> PROBST: Koror still with
a big with a big lead.
>> Left to right side.
You'll get taken off to do it.
Right side.
>> That's good,
that's good.
All right, now listen,
both sides.
>> Turn it around.
>> We're going the wrong way.
>> PROBST: Ulong,
the flag is that way.
( indistinct shouting )
>> Guys, let's freakin' paddle!
Ulong is looking for
another island.
>> Go. Go.
>> PROBST: Koror working
together, straight,
strong, fast.
>> Come on!
Come on!
>> PROBST: Ulong having a heck
of a time paddling.
>> Too many people on one side.
>> PROBST: Frustration setting
in for Ulong.
>> We're going to get it.
( whooping )
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Koror wins immunity
and reward!
>> Yeah!
( whooping )
>> Good strategy.
>> PROBST: All right, Koror,
nice strategy.
You chose to only bring fire.
You can boil water with that.
You can cook food with that.
Okay, here's immunity.
Yes, yes, yes!
You are safe from
the vote tonight.
One other decision.
Because you won,
you get a choice.
The two tribes will no longer
be living together on one beach.
You can either go back
to what you know
and the shelter
you help build,
or this is a map
to a new unknown beach
where you can start fresh.
>> But why see a beach
we already saw?
Let's go see something new.
>> New adventure.
>> PROBST: You're going
to take your chances.
>> We'll take our chances.
>> PROBST: Give up what you know
for the unknown.
>> Yes, we are.
>> PROBST: Here's your map
to your new home.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Ulong, good news is,
you're going home.
You're taking your
outrigger canoe with you.
Bad news is,
you're get some much-needed
practice when you paddle
to Tribal Council tonight
and officially vote out
the first member.
Get your stuff, head on out.
>> After the challenge,
we were so excited.
We won immunity,
and we won the stuff
that we needed to make fire.
We were so the underdog.
Winning that was huge for us.
( indistinct chatter )
This wave came,
and we went over.
I don't know what the deal was
with, you know,
who was leaning what way
or what, but I think
it was just a combination
of all forces,
and we just went down.
All of the supplies
to make fire
were in this heavy
steel container
that went straight down.
It was just like,
did this really happen?
>> I thought I saw something,
but hell, I don't know.
It may be right there.
>> We were so elated
the ride back in the canoe,
we were just loving life
and couldn't wait
to see the new beach.
And all this to happen,
we're just crushed right now.
And we don't have the water,
we don't have the flint
to start a fire to boil
the water and purify it.
We lost everything we won today.
We're in a worse scenario
than we originally had.
>> We lost to the challenge,
and we lost pretty hard.
The other tribe outplayed us
and outwitted us completely.
You know what,
we didn't make smart decisions.
They were smart,
they took just the fire.
>> The coconuts will sustain us
for 39 days if we had to.
So understand that--
I'm not going to allow
anyone to be negative.
>> Nobody needs to be negative.
>> Okay. No, no, about, "Oh,
we don't have this.
We got everything we need."
>> I know how things work.
I'm not the strongest person.
You know, people are gonna
choose who doesn't fit into this
and who they think
is a weak link.
So I definitely think
that I am a target.
>> But when it comes
to challenges, physically,
I know I'm stronger
than most of their dudes.
Well, let's keep on
what we was doing.
We're gonna do Angie...
>> Right. We're gonna do Angie.
But we got to get
the other guys to go in on it.
I want to go talk to Stephenie,
'cause we have issues.
If we have issues,
we need to work them out.
>> My vote will be for Angie
not because I don't like her,
but she is a person that
must be voted off
in order for our team
to be as strong as it can be.
>> So you think Angie.
>> I think we need
to keep the men.
I think it's absolutely...
>> We're keeping the men.
We can't lose any of our guys.
Which, I mean, seriously, I
mean, I-I could be voted off.
I don't want to be voted off.
I think the team needs me.
>> We need your strength.
But I do have to say,
we should've left earlier.
Yeah, you're right,
you're right, you're right.
I know that you're just
a complete go-getter,
and that's why you want us
to get everything,
and I understand that.
So I guess Angie.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. You, too.
>> Absolutely.
>> Okay.
Nervous as hell about Tribal.
Wish I wasn't going tonight.
We made a dumb mistake,
and I don't think
we should be going tonight.
But we are, and it's because
of one person, I feel.
The only reason
we lost the challenge
'cause we didn't
leave soon enough.
>> We didn't leave soon enough.
>> She wanted everything.
I don't think
we need to get rid of her.
I'm not gonna vote for her.
Stephenie's thinking
that Jolanda's the reason
we lost the challenge.
But that woman's got a lot,
a lot of strength.
I think she can still
help us out.
I haven't seen where
she's hurting us just yet.
>> Who do you want to vote for?
>> I think Angie right now.
>> She's not fit?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> All right.
Well, I don't know, I'm sorry.
( laughs )
>> No, that's good, that's good.
>> I'll go with you.
>> Okay, news flash, news
flash.
This is something
that I noticed.
For every two hours, that we
work, we're gonna rest
for at least an hour, okay?
It is time for us to get
focused, kick butt
and take names.
>> Jolanda is a strong
personality.
She is not a team player.
I didn't know that
that's how you guys felt.
>> Right.
>> I thought I was the only one.
Are you down with that?
Are you in?
>> Yeah.
>> Because I'll be pissed
if everybody changes their mind.
I mean, I'll hold it
against you for life.
>> Now she says,
"We're voting out Jo.
Are you in?"
I was, like,
"Hell, yeah, I'm in."
Like, I'm thinking
I'm the one out, like
I know how today went.
You don't think I remember
exactly the order
in which we got picked
for tribes?
I don't trust anyone
in this tribe.
But if I can at least
make it past this one,
I'll be happy.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach a flame,
dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual
of Tribal Council.
In this game,
fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire,
you're still in the game.
When your fire's gone,
so are you.
Have a seat.
Well, welcome to your first
Tribal Council.
I know you don't want
to be here.
Stephenie,
what's been the biggest surprise
first three days?
>> Biggest surprise?
Oh, God.
Starving,
we can't get fire,
we're so thirsty.
We were together as one,
and now we're separated,
we've formed bonds
and now they're gone,
and we don't know
what's coming next.
It's been really tough.
>> PROBST: James.
Happy with this tribe?
>> I am.
This is a damn fine tribe.
Everybody in here is tough,
they're young, they
got a lot of energy,
lot of testosterone.
We gonna win some matches.
We just didn't do it today.
>> PROBST: Jeff, let's talk
about the strategy
of today's challenge,
because it was about
making a choice.
And it seems as though
you guys have
a very strong tribe,
but it was brains
that beat you today.
Would you agree?
>> Yeah.
We've got the strength,
we all have the endurance.
There was just
a couple key times
that we just messed up,
and, you know,
we lost time trying
to get everything
we possibly could
and get running with it,
and... it wasn't gonna happen.
>> PROBST: So, James,
let me be clear.
You didn't even bring fire.
Oh, hell, no.
We should've.
You did not take fire?
>> Dumb-ass.
>> Well, we tried to get it,
but it was last,
and then when we realized that
we just lost a tremendous
amount of time,
we just said, okay,
just take the other stuff.
>> PROBST: Ashlee, is there a
leader on this tribe yet?
>> Jeff, I think that is...
the only thing
that's holding this group back,
is that we have yet to come
together as a group
and decide who is gonna lead
our group right now.
>> PROBST: Jolanda, can
this group lead itself...
as a group?
>> Uh, no.
We need somebody
to make a unilateral decision.
I mean, I would like,
if I could,
to help lead the team.
But I also know that I have
a very strong personality.
So, that's been
my biggest dilemma,
because I don't want
for people to say,
"Oh, you know,
"her personality's
too strong, she's bossy,
she's a... a witch."
>> PROBST: Angie, picked last,
tribe welcomes you,
but now here we are
at Tribal Council,
and you were still picked last.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: How heavy is that
weighing on your mind?
Or have you overcome that?
>> It weighs very heavy on my
mind. I mean, it's hard
being picked last.
But I think that I tried
really, really hard
at the challenge today,
but I think
definitely, my head was gonna be
on the chopping block.
You know, either there's
some things going on
where somebody has
somebody else in mind,
or it's just...
it's gonna overwhelmingly be me,
so...
>> PROBST: We'll find out.
It is time to vote.
Jolanda, you're up.
>> Um, Angie,
I just don't think that we can
be happy with losses.
We've got to evaluate
and move forward.
>> ( whispers ):
It's nothing personal,
but it's either you or I,
and I don't want it to be me.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave the
Tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Angie.
Jolanda-- one vote Angie,
one vote Jolanda.
Angie-- two votes Angie,
Angie.
That's three votes Angie,
one vote Jolanda.
Jolanda.
Three votes Angie,
two votes Jolanda.
Jolanda.
We're tied: three votes Angie,
three votes Jolanda.
That's four votes Jolanda.
First person voted out
of Survivor: Palau--
Jolanda.
That's five votes,
that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good luck, you guys.
Watch the way.
>> PROBST: Jolanda, the
tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, if there's one thing
you should take away
from tonight's Tribal Council,
it should be this:
You need to stop
with the excuses
and get a plan, or you will
be back here very soon.
You're not gonna be going
back to camp
with fire; you're gonna
earn that on your own.
Go back to camp. Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
( woman screams )
>> Oh, my God, there were three!
( thunderclap )
>> Oh, no!
>> PROBST: ...Koror questions
the move to the new beach.
>> Do you think there
could be a worse
island than this?
>> PROBST: At Ulong,
Jeff and Kim get cozy,
and the search
for flint intensifies.
>> Fire is the only thing
that matters.
>> I played this game,
and I don't think
that I would do
anything differently.
I mean, I am the oldest,
and I think differently
than my tribe.
They are a lot more
happy-go-lucky than I am,
but that's fine, because
this was a great adventure,
and it's an experience that
I think everyone should try,
and I don't regret
anything that happened out here.