>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor...
>> I can't step out from five to
side with one right now.
>> Uh-huh.
>> PROBST: Caryn knew she was
in the hot seat.
>> I'm just hoping and praying
that something happens.
Otherwise, I'm going home.
>> I did make a promise to my
girl.
>> PROBST: Ian made a promise to
Katie.
>> Katie and I had promised
each other if we won a challenge
we'd take each other, and
that's what we're gonna do.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Yacht, shower, big
feast.
All right, pick up your cubes.
We'll get started.
Tribe members were quizzed on
island knowledge.
Correct answer is...
"True." Gregg wins reward.
Obviously, it wouldn't be much
fun alone.
Gregg chose to take Jenn and
Katie along for the ride.
>> Hey, guys, I am so sorry.
I will, uh, pay you back.
>> Oh, no, we'll pay you back.
( laughing )
>> PROBST: Back at camp...
>> We have lost control of the
game.
>> PROBST: ...Ian realized it
was three against three.
>> I know they're ready to turn
on you, I know for a fact.
>> And you think Katie's in with
that?
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: So the three
concocted a risky plan to oust
Gregg.
>> I can go to Tribal Council
willing to take the rock.
I came to play a game.
>> That's the plan-- you and I
are both willing to choose
rocks.
>> Tom and I have decided that
we're gonna force a tie at the
Tribal Council.
We've prepared ourselves for
the idea that we might be going
home.
But this is a risk we had to
take.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, Gregg,
Jenn and Katie...
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: ...enjoyed a
surprise visit from their loved
ones... swam with dolphins...
>> Cheers.
>> Tom's a huge threat.
>> PROBST: ... and devised a
plan of their own.
>> It's us three to the final
three.
>> PROBST: Tom misses.
At the individual immunity
challenge, Ian shot his way to
victory.
Ian wins immunity!
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Moments before
Tribal Council...
>> Things going okay?
>> KATIE: Yeah.
>> PROBST: ...Ian pulled Katie
aside to let her in on the
plan.
>> Caryn and Tom and I are gonna
vote for Gregg.
>> What?!
>> I'm gonna have to make a
decision so I can have a better
chance of winning.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Ian's gamble paid off.
13th person voted out of
Survivor: Palau and the fourth
member of our jury, Gregg.
Katie joined him, Tom and Caryn
in voting Gregg out before a tie
was forced.
Gregg, the tribe has spoken.
Now it's down to five.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
( quiet squeaking )
>> Gregg turns out to be voted
out.
I had no idea, I was completely
blown away.
>> Oh... No, no, no, no.
>> He's definitely been a big
part of my existence out here
and keeping me comforted and all
that, especially at nighttime,
so...
( voice breaks ): Really
shocking.
>> But Jenn, you realize it
wasn't anything personal.
>> Absolutely.
You can't even... you've no
idea.
I was shocked for, like, two
seconds, and then I'm, like,
"Wow, okay, game on."
>> Jenn's a smooth operator,
man.
She's, uh, she handled it
surprisingly well.
I know she's fuming on the
inside.
You kind of have to step back
and-and take a look at it and
see, "Okay...
what's really going on here?"
Jenn's playing the game to win,
so, she's smooth, and, uh,
right now Caryn has some loyalty
to Tom, Katie has some loyalty
to me.
The only thing I'm worried about
right now is the three girls
turning on Tom and I.
If we can avoid that in the next
24 hours, uh, we're money.
>> The days are really numbered,
and I'm not taking anything
here for granted anymore.
>> You know I'm sticking around
for another couple days.
Uh, I don't know, I want to see
you stick around till the end.
I, uh...
>> How do you foresee this...
going off?
>> I mean, Katie's the one
who... we had an alliance,
and that was a good thing, and
the three of us were tight.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Um, and then Katie wavered,
so I don't know, I'd rather it
be you, me and Ian.
>> Yeah, so would I, but do you
think Ian will, um...
agree to knock off Jenn and then
Katie?
>> I think that's...
I don't see why not.
>> We need to, uh...
( whispers ): we need to take
out Caryn.
>> Even if Tom doesn't get
immunity tomorrow?
>> I mean, you guys willing to
take... take him out?
>> I don't know yet.
I don't know yet.
I'd say... I'd say...
>> Really?! Are you kidding me?
>> He's, like, your biggest
competition.
>> I know he is. But, like...
>> What are you thinking, are
you thinking "Nice guy, I want
to let him go to the top"?
>> No, I'm not thinking that at
all.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking,
um... I just don't want
to go back on...
You know what I mean? Like...
>> Go back on his word.
>> I hate going back on my word.
>> So you'd rather take out one
of us than...
than Tom-- that's insane.
>> I'd rather take Caryn out.
I'd rather take Caryn out
than...
>> You're safer with us, because
I know today Katie's gonna come
to you.
>> I know what's gonna happen
today, I know.
Katie's gonna come to you.
>> I know, she's gonna say the
three women have to go together.
>> Three women go together, get
rid of the guys, blah, blah...
>> Who do you have a better
chance against, Katie and me, or
Tom?
>> Right, right.
>> And I understand, I do.
I understand that people are
getting attached to people,
but, dude... you're talking...
>> Yeah.
>> ...a million dollars here.
>> Yeah, that's true.
>> There's a lot of things you
have to think about.
>> Uh-huh.
>> So you've got a lot to think
about, and if you're solid...
>> Yep. I'm solid with this.
>> I know you're not gonna go
with it.
>> Right.
>> Because it's not a good deal.
>> It's not a good deal.
>> You're just gonna
be the third one out, and...
>> Right.
>> If you're going to be the
third one out, what are you
playing for?
>> Right.
>> ( whispers ): Shoot!
Tom just told me his
strategy, that he wants Katie
and Jenn out of the picture
and the final three to be
himself, Ian and me, so I don't
know if I'm being played.
Uh, I'm just not sure right now.
He seems believable, but, um...
I don't know. I don't, uh,
really know what he's thinking.
This could be, you know,
just part of the planning
and the plotting in the last
six days.
Let's put it this way.
I'm guardedly optimistic about
my chance to make to it to the
final three.
>> "Up the creek again.
"A paddle could help you out.
"Where in the world are you?
"Far from home, no doubt.
"Use your passion and precision,
and by the time you're through,
"you'll enjoy the great tastes
of home
and Palau's most amazing view."
>> Oh, boy.
>> Let's do it, let's go.
>> This is a big decision we got
to make in the next two minutes.
What's going to happen?
Let's go over this quickly.
>> There's a possibility that,
after this reward challenge,
Ian and I, we're gonna get
separated.
If one of us gets to choose one
other person, we can't choose
each other on this one.
We've got to take one of
the girls out of the mix,
so that they're not going to,
uh, be able to throw it to each
other, so who do we take?
>> I don't know. Caryn.
Eh, we could take Katie.
>> Then we've lost... we've lost
Caryn, and she becomes a loose
cannon with three.
I don't... you trust Katie
that she's staying with the
final three?
>> Yeah, I do. I do.
She wants to go final three.
I trust her.
>> She flipped on us once.
Why would you trust her?
>> Tom likes Caryn 'cause he
can depend on her vote in a
final three situation.
I like Katie for the same
reason.
Our views conflict, but it's
just a matter of who's gonna
be the better salesman, and
it's an interesting discussion
that's going on, 'cause we're
getting down to the wire,
and you don't have very many
choices left.
>> Right now, we have two people
who think they're going to the
final two, and that's good.
>> That's true.
I thought it was gonna be easy
getting to the final four,
and now I know that it's not.
I feel like I'm on the edge
of a cliff, and I just hope I
remember to strap my parachute
on.
>> PROBST: You guys ready for
today's reward challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: This time I'm gonna
show you what you're playing for
before I tell you what the
challenge is.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: The winner of today's
challenge wins this.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: All new Chevrolet
Corvette, convertible.
Worth playing for?
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: All right.
Now let's get to the challenge.
Across the lagoon, there are
five pontoons, tied to each
pontoon is one of five colored
bags.
Using traditional Palauan
rafts, you will race across the
lagoon, retrieve the bag,
bring it back to your box.
Once you've collected all five
bags, open them-- inside the bag
you will find five mileage
markers.
These markers represent the
distance in miles from Palau
to five major cities.
Assign the markers to the right
city.
First person to do so correctly
wins a Corvette.
In addition, you've traveled a
long way for today's challenge
for a very good reason.
The winner of the Corvette
will drive out of here up this
jungle path to one of the most
remote and beautiful mansions in
Palau.
You'll have a barbecue feast.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: You'll spend the
night there, return to camp in
the morning...
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: When you get back to
the States, the car will be
waiting for you. Sound good?
>> Yeah.
>> Sounds great.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for
position, and we'll get started.
Here we go.
For reward, Survivors ready.
Go!
Tom's out first, followed by Ian
and Katie.
We got a traffic jam with Caryn
and Jenn.
You can go to any pole you want
in any order, but you can only
grab one bag on each trip.
Tom, going for his first bag,
Ian right there with him.
Tom has his first bag.
Ian has his first bag.
Katie going for her first bag.
Jenn right with her.
Ian and Tom racing back.
Caryn has her first bag.
Ian has his first bag, and he's
heading back out.
Going to run right into Tom
if he doesn't watch it.
Jenn back with her first bag.
( grunts )
Caryn moving in slow motion.
Men with a big lead.
Ladies have a lot of ground
to make up.
Ian has his second bag.
Tom has his second bag.
Caryn back with her first bag.
There's a head-on.
Just about takes Caryn out.
Ian back with his second bag.
Tom back with his second bag.
Jenn working for her second bag.
Ian unties his third bag,
looking for five bags total.
Tom right behind with his third
bag.
Jenn maneuvers back into her
dock with the second bag.
Ian has three bags
and he's heading back out.
Tom back with his third bag.
Tom and Ian both with three
bags.
Caryn with one.
Katie with one.
Jenn with two.
Katie back with her second bag.
Jenn has her third bag.
She's still in it.
Tom and Ian still dueling it out
neck and neck.
Ian noses Tom out.
Ian with four bags.
He's going out for his fifth and
final bag.
Tom gonna try and launch it,
and he misses.
Gotta get in and get it in the
box.
That's gonna cost him some time.
Katie struggling to get to her
third bag.
Corvette convertible on the
line.
Ian has his fifth bag, and he's
heading back.
Tom has his fifth bag, he's
Ian has all five bags.
Let's see how well he knows his
geography.
You gotta match the five mileage
markers up with the right city,
relative to how far they are
from Palau.
Ian thinks Manila is closest.
Jenn back with her fourth bag,
she's still fighting.
Caryn's slowing down more and
more.
Katie-- last place.
Tom now back with his fifth bag.
Ian deciding between London and
New York, which one's further
away.
He decides New York is the
furthest away.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Ian... has it right.
Ian wins reward.
>> Oh, man!
( kisses car )
>> PROBST: All right, Ian, get
over here.
>> Wow. Yeah! Get in there.
( sighs )
>> PROBST: You're gonna drive
this car from here, you're gonna
go up to a mansion, and you have
also earned the right to invite
one person to join you.
Who would you like to take with
you?
>> Well...
( Katie chuckles )
I made a deal if there was a car
involved that I would take Tom.
I told Katie yesterday that I'd
take her, but I-I shook hands on
it with him.
I made a promise to him, so I
can't, I can't break that.
>> PROBST: Tom, you're going
with Ian.
>> Have fun. Eat lots.
>> Thank you, guys. Thank you.
>> PROBST: All right.
Caryn, Jenn, Katie, nothing for
you.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
>> Can you believe the day
you're having?
>> This is one to put in the
books, for sure.
( Tom laughs )
>> Whoo-hoo-hoo!
I've never had a car before,
I've never had the money.
So a Corvette, it's pretty
fantastic.
Look at this!
>> Whoo! Oh!
>> It was a really neat reward.
A night at a mansion...
Whoo!
...with the best view in Palau.
And all the food you can eat.
It was gorgeous.
This is the best place to have
a party in the entire world.
>> Look at that.
That is yours.
>> You know, at first when I
first won it and I brought you,
I felt bad for Katie.
But she had turned her back
on me for the last challenge.
And she challenged me
thinking of getting me out
with Gregg's help, so...
So I don't feel that bad.
This is a good glass of
champagne.
>> But what we have to do is
bring her back into the fold
and convince her that we're all
going to play this thing to the
end.
>> Yeah.
>> We need to get back to our
original alliance of Tom, Ian
and Katie.
I'm hoping that Ian can bring
Katie around, because it really
is our only play.
>> Yeah.
Letting her know that
we're gonna be with her to the
end... a smart idea.
>> Yeah.
>> All right, what happened,
Katie?
>> Uh, well...
>> Tell me how the whole thing
went down.
>> The whole thing went down
since day one, Caryn.
I mean, Ian and I made a promise
to each other that, um, we would
stick together till the end.
Um, he pulled me aside yesterday
and was, like, "I'm telling you
right now, I'll choose you over
Tom.
You and I had a bond the first
day," and then he took Tom.
And I feel like I lost my best
friend out here.
Ian kept telling me, you know,
"I'll take you if I win.
I'll take you if I win."
And I was, like, "Okay, I'll
totally take you if I win."
It's a great deal to be made.
He won, and he picked Tom.
And so it meant my biggest,
closest ally out here is gone,
and that really bums me out.
And thinking about it, I mean,
when we were kind of at that
pivotal moment where it was
Steph was here, there was four
women, that was the time to make
a move, and we didn't make it.
But what I want to know is the
deal with you and Tom and what
your plan is.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't really have a deal
with Tom.
>> We know you have a deal with
Tom.
>> I don't have a deal with Tom.
Yeah, he tells me, yeah, he told
me he'll take me to the final
two, but he also told me that
he's... has a final three
with Katie and Ian, so...
>> Oh, really?
>> He told me...
>> Yeah.
>> Is that true, Katie?
>> Oh...
Katie just cleaned house.
She told everything, and I have
not known any of this
information.
And so, yeah, I'm a little wary
of Katie 'cause I think she's
been playing a real tough game
that I had no idea about.
>> Obviously, we know it's a
numbers game.
>> Mm-hmm
>> But one of the moves that you
have to make is when the person
that is in power starts to lose
that power, that's when you jump
over, and that's what just
happened today.
>> Uh-huh.
>> If it's Ian, we vote out Tom.
>> Right?
>> Yep. Right.
>> And if it's Tom...
>> Absolutely.
>> ... we vote out Ian.
>> That's right.
I'm all about that.
>> I love that.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Don't you think?
Yeah, I think.
>> I've told Jenn and Katie that
I am going with them.
This is the women's opportunity
to take the game.
But I have to really think who
do I have a better shot with,
the women taking out the guys
or the guys who are promising me
I'm going with them?
And I don't know.
>> Ian... it's a very immature
move today.
You just left three women...
And a... and a really upset...
like, best friend of yours...
>> One really upset best friend.
>> ...together? Don't go there.
>> A big mistake.
>> This is the only time to do
it.
It's the perfect time.
>> Yeah.
>> I need to talk to Katie.
>> Why don't you go to her right
now while they're sleeping?
>> Yep, okay.
>> All right, girly.
Full report.
>> No time to talk.
Ian, I need to ask you
a couple questions.
>> Yeah.
>> Just be straight up with me.
>> Anybody flip? Anyone...
>> I want to hear him.
I want to hear him.
>> Okay, go.
>> Is it you, me, Tom?
Or is it you, me, Katie?
>> It's gonna be you, me, K...
Er, you, me and Tom.
>> Why should I believe that
when Katie says you will never
let her down, that you'll take
her all the way?
>> If she stayed loyal.
She didn't.
>> Did you say that to her?
That's what you meant.
>> I told Katie at the very
beginning of the game
that, that I was playing the
game with her, right?
>> Yes.
>> I wasn't... I-I-I told Tom
I was not going to make a
decision until tonight.
That's the deal.
So it could have been you,
it could have been Katie.
>> If you haven't flipped with
the girls, it's you.
>> Right.
>> We're... like, we're all
playing the game.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> So I mean, I can't give you
an answer right now.
It would be unfair for me.
>> Okay, I appreciate that.
>> Now, what's the other half of
this? What's going on?
What's Katie saying now?
>> I don't want to say anything.
I don't want to say anything.
>> We're telling you the game,
our half of the game, you're not
telling us.
>> He didn't tell me anything.
He didn't tell me anything.
>> You just gave away her vote
tonight.
>> I don't think so.
>> You just screwed up.
Caryn had two options-- go with
the girls, or go with us and
trust the guys.
And Ian just wavers and said,
"Well, I can't promise and I
can't do this," and I just said,
"Oh, my God."
He better be really tight with
Katie.
>> Katie, we really need to
talk, we need to do it.
>> Well, that's actually the
last thing I'd like to do this
morning.
>> All right. Well, I'd still
like to talk to you.
It was like some horrible,
horrible nightmare.
It was like a bomb had exploded.
>> He's, like, "Can I talk to
you, Katie, soon as you get up?"
And I said, "Actually, that's
the last thing I'd like to do
this morning."
He's freaking.
>> It was a reward challenge...
for dinner.
This is like classic girl,
this is like girl troubles
back home.
I...
Nothing!
Can I have five minutes to talk
to you?
I don't want to talk about the
game, I don't.
>> It's all the game, Ian.
>> All right, well, can I have
five minutes to talk to you,
then?
Can you give me five minutes,
as opposed to listening to
everybody else?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Let's walk.
I won a reward challenge
yesterday, right?
48 hours earlier, the same thing
happened to me and to Tom...
>> Don't make me feel guilty
about that.
>> I'm not making you feel
guilty.
>> That was not something I
want, stop that now.
It's not about the reward
challenge.
>> Okay, all right.
Second point, no matter what
you heard from Caryn, no matter
what you've heard from Jenn,
I swore on this, that I...
there's no vote that would ever
go against you, ever.
That's the plan... that's still
my... that's...
I mean, I came in this morning
saying that's my plan.
I had every intention from the
very beginning of this game
to take you to the final two
and I told you that.
>> Who knows?
>> I feel like I'm dealing with
girl troubles back home...
>> Well, you know, I feel like I
lost my best friend yesterday.
>> How?
>> Listen to me for a second,
okay?
>> I am, I'm listening.
>> You promised me that you
would never lie to me and you
did yesterday.
I can't believe anything you say
to me.
I just... I can't.
I lost my best friend out here.
The closest thing I had to
family, you know?
>> Yeah, well...
>> And so, you're like, "I'll
take Tom, 'cause I can step all
over Katie."
>> No!
>> "She'll do whatever I say."
You didn't even think about how
that was going to make me feel
to have you totally go against
your word.
>> For, for... dinner?!
It's a little bit different...
>> It wasn't dinner, it was a
promise.
I was embarrassed.
( crying )
For you to come to me and tell
me, you know...
"Stay on this..." You went on,
and...
"Oh, and by the way, we're
voting off Gregg."
Nice intro. Nice intro.
>> I'm sorry. Like... I'm sorry.
Yeah, sometimes friends make
huge mistakes.
>> I realize that, I realize
that.
>> I wouldn't deliberately do
it, I'm a scatterbrain...
Like, and...
if you want me to step
out to show that it's true,
like, I mean, I'll do it.
I'll do it. Like...
I will, like...
>> I would never want you to do
that.
>> Just please know that,
that... over and above the
mistake that I made, that I hope
you can forgive me for it.
I'm gonna try to be your
friend for the rest of my life,
and if you don't want it, that's
fine, and, you know, I'll stay
away, but, like, the bottom line
is, like...
I'm off my rocker in
so many different ways, and...
I'm sorry. That's...
I mean, that's all I can say.
All right, I'm sorry.
Can I...?
>> Was Katie really put out by,
uh, not going, or was that just,
was that her way to jump out of
an alliance that she was looking
to break anyway?
>> I don't know.
>> I mean, you saw her...
Do you think...?
>> Katie's, Katie's a good
actress.
>> I know she's great.
( coughing )
>> I don't really know the
answer.
>> And did she bring up the
women's alliance, was it her
move?
Had they discussed who would go
first between Ian and I?
>> That's still up in the air.
I think immunity is key for
Tom and Ian, and they know it.
And I think they're desperate
and I think they're just
freaking out.
You know, the women are tired
of the guys pulling the strings
the entire game,
and now we're taking control.
>> Good morning, Koror.
We have mail.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Want to hear it?
>> Morning.
>> Good morning.
"You may have a memory
"like an elephant, but you
"better move like a gazelle.
"Brains and retention are
"paramount, but agility is
"required, as well.
"Concentration is only half of
"it.
"Losing focus would be a shame.
"Either move smart and swiftly
"or you could be next to leave
the game."
( groans )
>> Hmm...
>> At this point now, it's
scrambling.
You know, save your own neck,
and, uh...
You can take that alliance so
far, and then everybody looks
out for their own better
interests and it's usually
that weakest person in the
alliance who's gonna flop to
the other majority.
Katie's the weaker member, and
she's looking to better-deal us
now.
I don't hold it against her for
doing it, but that is the
reality of this game.
My whole game, Ian's whole game,
hangs on you.
And I want to convince you that
your whole game hangs on us.
>> Man, it's early for this.
>> Because even if you take...
Listen, I know.
But if you take one of us
tonight-- and we might, because
it's a concentration game--
so one of us goes home, the
other one's still here,
if that next one's physical,
and the guy who's left wins it,
then it's gonna be you.
>> I know.
>> And that'll be the payback
for flipping.
>> Yep.
>> So, then maybe you don't
get to the final two at all.
>> This morning I've been
bombarded by Tom
trying to bully me, and now,
once again, I won't get his vote
if I take him out.
And, um, my only chance to get
down to the final two is for me
to go with him and Ian.
I just don't know who to trust.
Well, you don't have to trust
anybody.
>> Yes, I do.
>> You go with what you know.
>> Tom sucks today, he's being
mean.
He's, like, threatening, and
it's, like, cold, and I don't
like it.
>> But you're going to make your
own decision, and...
>> I know, and I haven't made a
decision.
>> Really?
You're... Ian?
If you think that Katie's
with us, you're crazy.
>> She's in, I'm telling you.
>> She's playing you.
>> Maybe she is, but...
>> She is. She doesn't care
about the not going on the
thing.
She made that up just to save
face when she broke ranks with
us.
She's been waiting for her
opportunity and we gave it to
her-- why wouldn't she take it?
So the only thing now is to
threaten her back into the fold
by telling her, "If you betray
us after we carried you in those
early days..."
>> Right...
Attaching myself
with Tom right now, I'm becoming
a bigger target, 'cause Tom's
changed his method.
Um, he's getting really worried
and he's strong-arming people.
>> That's the only thing that
will keep her loyal.
>> I will, I'll talk to her.
I'll talk to her.
If I had my wits about me, I'd
take Caryn out, but if I had
my brain about me, I might need
to take Tom out tonight.
Like I said, the game's changed
from game domination to
self-preservation, so...
It's Survivor, not, uh, not
Parcheesi.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
First things first, Ian-- give
it up.
Once again, immunity back up for
grabs.
Well, you are 36 days in and
today's challenge will test
how much you have left--
both physically and mentally.
For today's immunity challenge
you will make your way
across a wobbly bridge, over
a series of floating pontoons.
You'll then navigate your way
across a rope bridge where you
will find a memory puzzle
containing 15 different images.
Memorize the position of as many
of those images as you can,
then make your way back
where you will find your own
empty memory puzzle grid.
Start duplicating that puzzle.
First person to correctly
duplicate their memory puzzle
wins immunity.
Couple rules--
if you fall off an obstacle,
go back to the beginning of that
obstacle.
If you think you have your
memory puzzle solved
and you call out and I check it
and you're wrong, you gotta go
back and take another look
before you can make any changes
so, make sure you're right.
One note-- each puzzle is
unique, so looking next door at
your neighbor's will do you no
good.
We'll draw for positions and
we'll get started.
All right, here we go, for
immunity, and a guaranteed
spot in the final four.
Survivors ready...
go!
Caryn and Katie down in the
first obstacle.
Katie's caught up in it.
Jenn, Ian, Tom, making good
time.
Tom almost goes down.
Jenn across, Ian across.
Katie and Caryn still back at
the start.
>> Oh, I know.
>> PROBST: Jenn, Ian, Tom,
making mental notes.
Caryn struggling.
Tom first to head back, Ian
right behind.
Jenn taking a long time to make
some notes.
Tom, struggling to hang onto
that bridge and he does.
Tom and Ian both working on
their puzzles.
How much do they remember?
Tom puts the first row together,
and he's heading back.
Katie's across.
Caryn's across.
Everybody's in it.
Ian heading out for another
look.
Jenn finally heading back.
Jenn goes right to work,
wasting no time, lots of images.
Caryn on her way back.
Ian takes a second peek, on his
way back.
Jenn puts her entire board
together.
Not ready to call out whether
she has it.
Tom's back.
Katie making her way back.
Jenn heading back to the master
grid.
Everybody working fast.
Ian heads back for another look.
Ian checks his board and heads
back.
Caryn, struggling with the
wobbly bridge.
Ian just runs across.
Tom takes a big hit, and he's
down.
Gotta go back to the beginning.
Ian thinks he has it.
You're not right.
Ian calls it out, something's
wrong.
He's got to head back before he
can make any changes.
Ooh!
Tom goes down hard again, but
he's still on it.
Good recovery.
Jenn working hard on her puzzle,
she's still fighting.
Tom's back.
Jenn heading back to the master
grid.
Ian trying to figure out what he
did wrong.
>> Jeff, I think I got it.
>> PROBST: Tom thinks he has it.
Tom's not right.
Slow down and really pay
attention.
Look at these images.
Caryn not giving up.
Katie taking more notes.
Caryn working it.
Tom's heading back.
Ian heading back.
Katie still in it.
Did Ian figure out what he had
wrong?
>> Jeff?
>> PROBST: No. No. No. Back.
Ian called it out, didn't have
it, headed back.
Jenn back to work on her puzzle.
Can she solve it?
>> Okay, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Tom thinks he has it.
Tom has it right!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Tom wins immunity!
>> Whew.
>> PROBST: Tom, get over here.
>> I don't have to go across
the bridge...
>> PROBST: No more bridges.
You've earned a fair walk.
Guaranteed spot in the final
four.
Tom, the only person safe
at tonight's Tribal Council.
Ian, Caryn, Jenn, Katie, one of
you is going home.
We'll see you there tonight.
Head on back to camp.
>> One... two... three.
Looks good.
I said this morning that
immunity was about as important
as it's ever going to be for me
today, and, uh... I pulled
another one out of the hat.
Just got lucky.
There may still be a female
alliance, and they may be taking
out Ian tonight, and, uh, if
he's gone-- um, and I've done
everything I can to keep him
here-- then it's an alliance of
three against me,
and any immunity I don't win,
I'm gone.
>> I was number one to get rid
of Caryn.
I was like, "Please can we take
her out?"
>> Right.
>> But...
>> My mistake? I was stupid.
I was stupid on both levels, on
friendship and game.
>> Just made me reconsider
who...
>> Right.
>> ...you're loyal to.
>> I know that you... You know,
maybe all bets are off now with
you, and... I mean... I men...
>> I don't know, that's...
I told myself yesterday I would
not make...
>> Any promises.
>> ... any promises.
>> To anyone.
>> This is the, this is the
clincher.
>> Yup.
>> This is my test.
( talking indistinctly )
>> After tonight, it's a
one-in-four chance of winning a
million dollars, and people are
going to be very scheming and
conniving to get it.
>> Big day.
>> Big day. Big day.
>> Big day. For somebody.
I am fearing what Katie will do
because Katie's holding the
cards right now.
Katie can decide to send Ian
home, or she can send Jenn and I
home.
I don't know, I hope that she's
being genuine.
If not... Jenn and I have made
a mistake.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury.
Coby, Janu, Steph and Gregg,
voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
Let's talk about the reward
challenge.
Ian wins, he's got to pick
somebody to go with him, and he
chose Tom.
Katie, you didn't seem too happy
about it.
>> No, I was... that was the
darkest day I've ever had out
here.
It wasn't about going and
eating a steak or driving in his
Corvette.
It was about a promise that he
made to me, and... he just broke
it.
I had no idea he had a different
thing going on with Tom.
It just made me rethink
everything that's happened in
the past 33 days, and...
I don't know what to believe.
>> PROBST: Ian, did you
anticipate how tough it was
going to be on Katie?
>> It was the biggest mistake
I've made in the game.
It was the biggest, biggest
thing, and not even from a game
standpoint, but from the fact
that I really hurt somebody that
I care about.
And that, I, you know, Katie's
my... like, one of the closest
people that I've-I've...
No, the closest person I've
gotten to out here, and I made a
decision that hurt her.
And I felt really bad.
>> PROBST: Worried that it might
cost you?
>> Yeah, sure. Sure.
>> PROBST: Caryn. It's not a bad
thing to see two people out of
the five having a tiff.
>> Honestly, that tiff was a
revelation, because after Gregg,
Jenn and Katie went on the
yacht, the minute we landed on
the beach, Ian says to me, "If
we don't vote off Gregg and
Jenn and Katie, they're going
to run the game."
And he devised this whole
strategy that if I would go with
Tom and Ian, I would be in with
them.
And then, after the whole thing
with Ian taking Tom on the
reward, and Katie saying,
"Well, he's made these promises
to me and he swore on his
cross."
And I'm thinking, "Oh, my gosh,
he's promising me this and he's
promising Katie this."
So, this is a revelation.
These guys are running the game,
and I felt really had.
>> PROBST: Caryn, you just
opened the vault and put four
people on their heels.
>> I-I'm sorry, I've had it up
to here.
I'm just telling it the way it
happened.
And I think the jury needs to
hear really what's going on.
I mean, they're going to be
deciding who gets a million
bucks.
>> PROBST: There's a lot of
accusations being made.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Ian, a lot of fingers
pointing at you tonight.
>> We went... we went about the
plan, and we took Gregg out.
But Caryn's just as much a part
of it as the three of us were.
Gregg needed to go.
And I want to make it clear
that-that I never had any
intentions of voting off
Katie, and Jenn, for that
matter.
>> It's baloney.
>> That's not true.
>> PROBST: Tom?
>> What happened when we got
back to the beach now, Caryn has
informed me that Katie and Gregg
have decided I'm the next to
go...
>> ( gasping ): Oh...
>> ...so they said it's her,
and then me.
>> My gosh! Tom!
>> No?
>> You are such a liar.
>> Oh!
>> Tom, I made one promise to
you.
And the promise that I made to
you was that if I ever heard
your name mentioned, I would
tell you about it.
>> If I could finish my half of
this story.
>> Okay, fine.
>> I talked to Ian, and Ian said
"Well, if Gregg is targeting
you, you're number five, I'm
number four, Gregg's got to go."
>> Right, exactly.
>> That's where the decision was
made.
>> PROBST: So you guys suddenly
are at the bottom, and you want
to remedy that.
>> Right.
>> Ian so did not trust Katie
that he didn't tell Katie until
five minutes before we left for
Tribal Council that Gregg was
going out.
Because he was so concerned
that she was going to run...
>> Absolutely not true.
>> ...to Gregg and to Jenn.
>> Katie knows when it was,
so she knows.
>> It was actually right before
we left.
>> PROBST: Ian, why didn't Katie
know?
>> Well, what's, like, what's
the benefit to me to Katie not
knowing ten minutes before or
three hours before?
>> Because you're telling me,
you're telling me what's
happening rather than me saying
"Okay, let me think on that."
Maybe I might want to go with
Jenn and Gregg.
It's kind of like strong-arming
once again, which keeps
happening.
>> That wasn't the intention.
>> No, but that...
>> Right.
>> I have no idea what's
happening here, I'm just saying.
Looking at it now, it's like...
>> Okay.
>> "Oh, really, is that what
happened?"
>> PROBST: So what are you going
to base your vote on?
>> Honestly, I don't know what
I'm doing.
>> PROBST: Okay. Tom, based on
everything that's gone on
tonight, I'm sure I don't even
have to ask about you giving up
immunity.
All right, time to vote.
Ian, you're up.
>> Best three seconds of my day.
Can't wait for you to go home.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read
the decision is final,
person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Ian.
Caryn.
One vote Caryn, one vote Ian.
Two votes Caryn, one vote Ian.
14th person voted
out of Survivor: Palau,
the fifth member of our jury,
Caryn.
That's three, that's enough,
you need to bring me your torch.
Caryn, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
You are the final four.
Over the next three days, you
will have three Tribal Councils,
two immunity challenges, one
winner.
I can't wait to see how this
plays out.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> It's good to be final four!
>> PROBST: With only three days
left...
>> We were able to just enjoy
each other, even though we're
about to slit each other's
throats.
>> PROBST: ... the drama
intensifies.
>> I told them that I was gonna
vote you out.
>> Okay.
That's all I needed to know.
>> PROBST: Join us for the
two-hour finale, and find out
who will be the sole Survivor.
>> Sorry to be the bearer of bad
news, but too bad, all that
stuff happened.
You know, you want to shoot the
messenger, go ahead and shoot
the messenger, fine with me.
See where it gets you in the
end.
Everybody's been very
deceptive, and I'm the one who
starts speaking about it, and...
you ultimately have to face the
music anyway.