PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, the physical nature
of the game took its toll on
Yaxha.
>> Everybody over here at Yaxha
has these things all over
them.
Got a long way to go on the game
so probably gonna get a lot
more banged up than this.
>> PROBST: At the challenge the
tribes competed for a sweet
reward.
Today you are playing for
chocolate.
>> Oh, my God.
Also, the winning tribe will get
a chance to take part in a zip
line canopy tour of the jungles
of Guatemala.
Survivors ready? Go.
Nakum fell behind.
Bobby Jon is out.
Nakum panicking.
As Yaxha sprinted to victory.
Yaxha wins reward.
Flying high from their win,
Yaxha took the ride of their
life.
>> We got to swing through the
jungle on these cables and felt
just majestic.
>> PROBST: And at the end of the
tour they found their chocolate
feast.
>> I'm gonna remember today for
two reasons.
The day I went rip cording
through a jungle, and the day
that I ate the most chocolate
I have ever eaten in my
entire life.
>> PROBST: The next day Yaxha
surprised Nakum with a visit.
>> Hi!
>> Oh, what are you guys up to,
man?
>> It's my birthday so we
figured we would invite you for
a pool party.
>> PROBST: At the party, Jamie
didn't like the idea of the two
tribes meeting.
>> I was worried that maybe
Stephanie was getting along too
well with other people, maybe
she would, you know, form bonds
there.
I'm here for business.
And everyone else should be
also.
>> PROBST: For immunity the
tribes raced to unearth pieces
of a puzzle.
They're heavy with that sand.
The game was close but Nakum
assembled their puzzle first.
Nakum wins immunity!
Back at Yaxha, Amy felt she was
next to go.
>> I knew going into this if we
didn't win the immunity I had an
uphill battle.
>> PROBST: But Brandon and Danni
were still undecided.
>> I was hoping it wouldn't come
to this, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm conflicted because here I
have my alliance with Bobby Jon,
but I believe that Gary and Amy
maybe deserve to be here a
little bit more than he does.
>> PROBST: With Bobby Jon and
Amy both at risk, the tribe
voted out the weaker of the two.
Then the game took an unexpected
turn.
The four of you will not go back
to your camp.
You will go directly to Nakum's
camp.
All of your personal items, all
the rewards you've won, will be
relocated.
You are going to merge into one
new tribe.
Ten are left, who will be voted
out tonight?
( theme song playing )
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
(animals calling)
>> We just went to Tribal
Council and then Jeff turns to
us and says here is your new
buffs, you are not going back to
your camp, you are heading over
to Nakum for a merge.
>> We were walking up to the
Nakum camp for the first time;
myself, Danni, Brandon and Gary,
and we just told each other
look, hey, we're in this thing
together, and we don't know
what's going to happen.
>> I twisted my ankle.
>> It was real tough for me to
walk in here tonight because I
can't be around Stephanie for
more than five minutes without
wanting to vomit.
And I can't be around Jamie for
more than five minutes without
wanting to knock him out.
So I don't know what I'm going
to do.
>> We have some new buffs for
you.
>> Hey!
>> Oh, my God.
>> Gary.
>> What's up, big fella?
>> What's going on?
What happened?
>> Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
>> Who got voted out?
>> Amy.
>> They brought us straight
from tribal.
>> Are you freaking kidding?
>> Merge, baby, merge.
>> Hey, ya'll, why don't you
come over here and get a buff.
>> These are nice, huh?
>> And they don't stink.
>> Yaxha came here immediately
after Tribal Council and
basically gave us new buffs and
told us there was a merge.
So we were all thrown for a
loop.
My head is, like, spinning.
>> Come on, let's get that fire
started.
>> I just came into camp and
started doing my thing, man.
Right when I started getting the
fire, here comes Jamie over
there.
>> There's not room in the
shelter.
I hope they don't mind sleeping
outside.
>> He said something smart, I'm
just like, "Dude, you going
to say one more thing to me I'm
going to knock every one of your
teeth slam out of your head."
>> Ooh. Is that a log?
>> Yeah.
>> Wow!
>> Bobby Jon is just looking for
something to do, man.
(laughter)
>> I ain't trying to be the
hero.
>> You gonna chill out, brother,
or what?
>> This morning woke up, and,
you know, like I mean it wasn't
a dream after all.
We really merged and everything.
And you know, a new tribe.
And you think, "Whee," you know,
one big happy family.
That's not how it works.
(scoffs)
>> I don't think we have any
more wood to get.
I think you're okay.
Why don't you sit down?
>> Nakum, we came over...
I didn't think they were that
warm and friendly.
Brandon, Bobby Jon and myself,
I think Gary does, too,
we feel kind of like we are
slaves, because we know our
head's on the chopping block and
we will try to do what you can
to stick around.
But you feel like an outsider.
>> This whole deal kind of
sucks.
You know, there's four of us
from the Yaxha tribe and six of
them from the Nakum tribe.
>> Now we can make room on the
fire.
Should we put it on the grill or
what?
>> I think myself or Bobby Jon
are probably gonna be first on
the chopping block.
We are probably most likely to
get immunity, so they want to
get those guys out first.
And things aren't looking very
up to tell you the truth.
>> I hope it's not a freakin'
Reward Challenge.
We'll open tree mail and
there'll be a pig inside.
>> Or a Mayan feast.
Oh, my God.
It's a basket.
What is it?
>> Okay, here we go.
>> "Congratulations, you are now
one tribe.
Here's your new flag and paints
for you to add to your new tribe
name.
If you are feeling bored around
camp or could use some peace of
mind in this game, there is a
small individual immunity idol
hidden in the woods.
This is in addition to any
individual immunity you win at
challenges.
It is about six inches tall and
is made of stone."
>> What?
>> "Find it and you have power.
You can use it at any time to
save yourself.
"You don't need to tell anyone
you have it, but if are you
going to use it, you must
"present it at any Tribal
Council before the vote."
>> "But the idol's powers expire
when are you down to the Final
Four."
>> So hidden somewhere in the
woods there is an idol that will
give us immunity that we can use
at any Tribal Council up to the
Final Four.
Somewhere there's individual
immunity hidden in the woods
to use any time you want.
>> We got tree mail saying that
there's a little immunity idol
about this big in a jungle
that's this big.
>> So the search is on.
Finding the secret immunity idol
could be huge for anyone.
If you use it right, you can
almost guarantee yourself to the
Final Four.
>> You checking this area out?
>> I think it's going to be
someplace around the temple,
don't you?
>> If I find the idol, I am not
telling anybody.
I wouldn't come prancing into
camp saying, "Hey, I found the
idol."
No way. I wouldn't do it.
>> It's going to be like finding
a needle in the hay stack.
You could be looking for days
and days and days for the damn
thing and still not find it.
And I got a target right on my
head, you know.
And so I could really use it.
Like, really.
>> Got to find that idol, man.
>> Bobby Jon was looking for the
idol.
And he said, "I'm not asking for
an alliance or anything like
that."
He's like, "I'm just asking to
help me out so at least I make
the jury this time."
And I said, you know, "I totally
understand but I can't make any
promises."
It's going to be either him or
Brandon that goes.
>> Good morning, everyone.
So, have we thought of a name?
Anybody?
>> What's that?
>> Have we thought of a name?
>> What are you thinking, Cindy?
>> Take the two names and blend
them.
>> Yeah.
>> Xhakum.
>> I like that.
That sounds catchy.
Ba-ba-boom, Xhakum. Hey!
>> I wanted to get our new
Xhakum flag started.
Xhakum to us means to us Yaxha
and Nakum put together.
So we are one big happy tribe,
right now.
Everything is A-OK.
>> Oh, it's so beautiful, you
guys.
>> That looks nice, huh?
>> Xhakum.
Very nice.
Look at that.
>> What's up?
>> The quest for the idol is
still under way.
I can tell you where it is
not, back there.
>> It's not back there?
>> Mm-mm.
>> Also not back there.
>> That idol could be worth a
million dollars.
I have been looking for it
because I don't want any of the
old Yaxha to have it.
That would put a hurting on my
plan.
>> I've got to take a leak.
Maybe I will take a leak all
over that idol.
>> Me, Gary, Danni and Brandon
up here are sitting ducks pretty
much.
So I spend about an hour each
day looking for the immunity
idol, because I'm not done yet.
It's going to be found.
That's the thing.
It's going to be found for sure.
We just don't know when or who's
going to find it.
And you can drive yourself nuts
looking for it.
>> So you went to that place
over there where we get all the
wood?
>> I'm not even going to look
any more.
It's driving me crazy.
I have to take a break for a
little bit.
I mean I'm exhausted, man.
Up and down, up and down, up and
down.
>> Let's just go chill then.
>> I really want to find it.
I really feel like it's here but
I cannot find it anywhere.
And I'm horrible at looking for
things.
I'm just the worst person at
finding anything in the world.
So my odds of getting this
immunity idol are a little bit
low.
( insects buzzing )
I'm searching for the immunity
idol and I reach up and put my
hand, like, in a hornet's nest
at the top of this temple.
I just got attacked by hornets.
I'm done.
That was just the signal from
the Mayan gods that I am not
meant to find this idol.
>> What you doing there, big
guy?
>> I'm just going to make a
couple more flies up, just in
case.
>> For all those big fish we're
going to catch.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> Fish fry.
>> Yeah.
I was really expecting
some sort of food.
Because it seems like in the
game of Survivor whenever a
season merges or the teams
switch, or anything big happens
where people come together,
there is always food involved.
And I mean, an immunity idol
like that is cool and all, but
we're like starving.
So I would much rather feast.
But whatever.
Survivor.
>> This will be the first time
there's ever a merge without
a celebration.
>> That's pretty sad.
>> I'm sad already.
>> You know, we had camp over at
Yaxha, it was positive.
We had fun.
We all got along.
And come over here, and it is
just like, they just complain
all the time.
>> Come on.
Two days into the merge already
and we didn't have a feast?
>> That's retarded.
>> I'm bored out of my mind,
too.
>> It was just so negative here
at camp.
I mean, just complaining about
not having food or not having
anything to do.
And so we just said we needed to
get out, get away for a little
bit.
Go fishing.
>> Do you want to go fishing?
>> Ready?
>> Yeah, fishing.
>> Keep dreaming, baby.
>> Is there any chocolate left?
>> Do we have any honey left?
>> We are devils.
>> I don't care. They went
fishing and it's a slap in the
face, you know?
>> I can't believe they are all
really that dumb to all go
together.
>> If they were even strategic
they wouldn't have gone all
together to go fishing because
they wouldn't leave us six
here to plot our next plan.
>> You know, we can hang out and
eat honey while they go fishing.
I'm not, like...
I'm not totally cool with that
kind of like that kind of
attitude like we are in control
now.
So we don't have to do anything.
And we have to make them do
everything.
>> It's like we're at war, man.
Prisoners.
We have to do all their bitch
work and they get to raid all
our resources and all our other
stuff that we worked hard to
acquire.
>> They went right through our
stuff when we came over.
Didn't even ask.
>> Like a bunch of pigs.
>> All right, let's do this.
Whoever catches the biggest fish
goes home first.
>> Yeah, whoever catches the
biggest fish goes home first.
>> You guys are crazy.
>> How does that sound?
>> I kind of had this really sad
realization.
Am I a member of the axis of
evil?
>> Man, they better bring some
fish back.
>> They better get their ass up
tomorrow morning, too.
Before they catch a damn six
footer, man.
>> Bashing people when they are
not around to bring group unity
is not a pretty way to play this
game.
>> Let's make sure we got it.
>> So Brandon. Brandon...
>> Is that what we said?
>> Brandon, Bobby Jon and then
Danni.
>> Right.
>> Stephanie bitches a lot, man.
>> She sure does.
All they do is complain.
>> They complain so much.
Talk about food, complain.
You ain't going to eat on
Survivor.
They ain't never ate on
You ain't going to eat on this
Survivor.
You ain't going to eat on the
next Survivor.
So why you want to talk about
it?
>> If we are smart we will go
ahead and not worry about it,
and we'll just keep knocking
them off like we wanted to.
>> Knock them out one by one.
>> Nobody over there is going to
save anybody's ass.
They are all out there for
themselves.
That is how it was in the old
tribe.
>> It's not time to be nice
anymore.
It's time to protect our
investment of, you know, blood
and sweat, and it's time to let
those guys go home.
>> We're awesome and everybody
else sucks.
>> I say they are some of the
most wonderful people I ever met
in my life.
>> I'll say it right back.
All of them.
(laughter)
(overlapping chatter)
>> Nice, nice having this pool
right next to our camp.
Unfortunately, our beach is like
quicksand so it had to be
anchored out here, so we come
and go as a tribe, which is kind
of nice.
For those days that we're really
bored and our days off and
stuff, we just hang out here and
just enjoy ourselves.
>> Everybody just kind of
hanging out, kind of waiting on
tree mail, to be honest with
you.
I don't think, I don't know,
I just don't think that the
Nakum's fairy tale right now is
going to quite come true.
They really think that those six
are going to make it down to the
final six.
But for some reason I just don't
think that's going to happen.
>> It's a box.
>> What the heck?
>> I don't know.
A message.
>> "'I don't need practice,'
former Survivors have said,
'carrying a pot around on my
head.'
So if you feel safe,
"ignore this note, and be
prepared to cast your next
vote."
>> Balance a pot?
>> Holy cow.
Who wants to try it?
>> I bet Lydia is good, she has
a low center of gravity.
>> We just have to stand there
with a damn pot on our heads.
You're a pot head.
>> This is going to be the first
individual immunity challenge.
So it's going to be quite
interesting.
A lot of heads are going to be
rolling today.
>> I'm standing with it.
>> I can stand all day with it,
it's the walking.
>> That's the whole challenge.
>> I keep telling myself I'm not
out of this sucker yet.
Just get pumped up.
And that's what I got to do to
win because I've got a long road
ahead of me, if I'm going to do
this.
>> I have a dome-shaped head, so
I'm S.O.L.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh, God.
>> PROBST: How is everybody
doing?
>> Pretty good.
>> PROBST: First thing's first,
take back the idol.
And I will take back the old
buffs.
Don't need the buffs any more.
Immunity idol is of no longer
any value.
Individual immunity is what you
covet from here on out.
So catch me up.
What's the new name of the
tribe?
>> Xhakum.
>> PROBST: Xhakum.
How'd the merge go down?
There was a few of you guys
that were probably sleeping when
you got some visitors.
Jamie, what was it like for you?
>> I was thinking there is not
room in the shelter, hope they
don't mind sleeping outside.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, what kind
welcome is that to say, "Hey,
you know, we don't have enough
room for everybody so some of
"you are gonna have to sleep
outside?"
>> I'm not going to
ever pour myself on anybody.
I would just soon as sleep in a
tree with the howling monkeys.
It don't matter to me.
I'm out here to play the game
and do what I've got to do.
>> PROBST: Cindy, anything you
expected coming with the merge
that didn't come?
>> I think we all expected some
sort of a snack or you know a
treat, some sort of celebration
because, you know, we've all
come together.
It's almost like you know, a new
start.
But here it was, all we have is
corn and nuts and hauling water.
>> PROBST: Well, it is true that
in the past part of the
tradition of a merge has been a
merge feast.
That tradition will continue
today, but with a twist.
If with Tribal Council looming
tonight you still feel very
secure in this tribe, don't
really think you need immunity
around your neck, you don't have
to participate at all.
Instead you can plop over here,
have a seat behind the feast and
eat and eat and eat.
If on the other hand you feel
like maybe are you a little bit
in trouble, your head might be
on the chopping block, you can
opt to take part in the
challenge.
But if you participate in the
challenge, you don't eat.
>> Oh, my God.
>> You will each have in your
hand one ramon nut and one jade
bead.
When I tell you to, you're
going to show me the one
that tells me what you want to
do.
Jade represents challenge.
Ramon nut means "I want to eat,
I'm not going to take part in
the challenge."
Everybody got your choice?
Three, two, one, reveal.
Rafe feels confident.
He's eating.
Take a spot over there behind
the feast.
Gary is going to participate in
the challenge.
Bobby Jon's gonna be in the
challenge.
Jamie is hungry, take a spot in
the feast.
Steph feels lucky, take a spot
in the feast.
Judd is going to participate in
the challenge.
Cindy is in the challenge.
Brandon is in the challenge.
Lydia is going to fill her
belly-- take a spot behind the
feast.
Danni is in the challenge.
You guys can go and take a
spot, but don't start eating
yet.
All right, let me explain the
challenge.
You are going to balance a clay
pot on your head for as long as
you can.
You cannot touch the pot with
your hands.
If you do you are out.
You cannot step off a small cube
which you will be standing on.
Last person left standing with
that pot on their head wins
immunity, is safe tonight at
Tribal Council.
If after one hour we are still
going, we will move to a tie
breaker.
Make sense?
We'll get started.
Everybody's pot is in place and
this challenge has begun.
You can start eating.
>> Oh, my God.
>> It's good.
>> This is so good.
>> PROBST: How's the food?
>> Good.
>> Mmm. Very good.
>> PROBST: Did you expect to see
four people sitting down to eat?
>> Brandon and Bobby Jon know
they have a chance to go home
tonight.
They are the best two athletes
in the group.
I think Judd wants to protect
our lead.
I look up to him for it.
>> I thought we were one tribe.
>> You know it's not one tribe.
>> Yeah, but...
>> So why are you saying that
right now?
>> Well, because I can.
And I will.
And I want to.
>> PROBST: Well, Jamie so you le
the cat out of the bag.
So clearly it is no big secret.
You said Judd is up there
"protecting our lead."
Whose the "our"?
It must be you four and Judd.
So it's tribal lines all the
way.
>> Yup.
>> I have been knowing the whole
time what is going on.
>> Bobby Jon, you knew you had
to win immunity today, bud.
>> I'm not trying to, it's just
when you start going off at the
mouth I'm ain't gonna let you
big boy me though.
>> PROBST: You are 30 minutes in
Never has 30 minutes seemed so
long.
>> Good job, Judd.
>> How are you doing, Bobby Jon?
Good?
>> Are you consciously trying to
rub it in?
>> PROBST: Danni makes the
slightest move, Danni's out.
Take a spot on the mat.
And we are reaching the end of
the hour.
Five, four, three, two, one.
You're there.
Cindy, Brandon, Gary, Judd,
Bobby Jon, moving on to a tie
breaker.
Slowly bring your hands up to
your pot.
Step down.
>> Good job, guys.
(applause)
>> PROBST: Let's go.
Head over to the pyramid.
For the tie breaker, you will
race up the steps of the
pyramid.
No hands can touch your pot at
any time.
First person to the top or the
person who goes the furthest,
without breaking their pot wins
immunity.
Here we go, guys. Survivors
ready?
Go!
Gary and Brandon moving out
quickly.
Bobby Jon right behind.
Cindy's out.
It's Gary and Brandon.
Bobby Jon coming up.
Brandon's out.
Bobby Jon's out.
>> Way to go Gary!
>> PROBST: Gary wins immunity.
Nice job.
>> Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Gary, the only person
safe from Tribal Council tonight
unless someone finds the hidden
immunity idol or perhaps has
already found it.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who is going home.
See you at tribal.
Head on back.
>> I swear right now, I'm not
eating again.
>> I don't care what you do.
You guys can do whatever you
want.
I don't care what you do.
>> Unless everybody's going to
eat, I'm not eating.
>> You know me, I don't care
what you do.
You want to eat, you eat.
You don't want to eat, you don't
eat. I don't care.
I was just going in there to
compete, man. That's it.
>> Me? 'Cause you're so hot?
>> I think everybody should shut
up, I'm concentrating and you
keep yapping your mouth,
I'm like "Dude, shut up, man.
Shut up, man.
I can't listen to you right
now."
>> Yaxha, we came into the merge
with just four people.
And Nakum had six.
And so obviously Jamie called it
out today.
We knew our head was on the
chopping block.
But he really called it out
today.
I thought he was very cocky,
very arrogant and just a slap in
the face.
>> It wasn't like we were like
are not welcome here and get
lost.
>> Jamie did not show class at
the challenge whatsoever.
And I think everyone agrees on
that.
People are seeing this nature in
him, this immaturity and they're
not liking it very much.
Even Judd's just like, the
dude's got keep his mouth shut.
>> Dude, shut up, man, shut up.
Argue later or don't even argue
at all, man.
>> We told him again and again
just keep some of your thoughts
to yourself.
Because I think it's starting to
come around.
It may come around and get him.
>> I just feel so crappy today,
you know what I mean?
Because like, I know who I want
to be voting with.
>> Yeah.
>> I've kind of been asking
myself like why are you
sleeping with the devil,
almost.
And today at the feast it was
like everything just
crystallized in front of my
eyes.
I cannot respect myself and go
far in this game with Jamie.
>> We're just basically saying
that Jamie is getting a little
too cocky and he's not...
>> I am not going to tell him
anymore.
I'm not here to baby-sit nobody.
>> Right. And we've told him.
>> I told him twice.
>> Oh, we are supposed to stand
there and take it.
>> You didn't say a damn word.
You can't talk when we are in
the middle of a challenge.
>> I know.
>> Jamie is being an idiot right
now.
And he's sitting there, digging
his own hole in his own tribe.
He's probably going home
tonight.
I see these people in this
tribe, and they're like, they
can't take him anymore.
He's being arrogant, he's being
cocky.
All he does is mouth off and go
to challenges.
At the immunity challenge I was
thinking what if I slipped off
this platform with this bucket
on my head and smashed it over
his head?
>> I was telling Brandon, it
sucks, you know, but if you are
the best athlete here, you're
going to be going, you know?
>> I don't think like that.
I look at people's character.
>> If you had your choice, who'd
be going home?
>> Man, I ain't even thinking
about it right now, Jamie, to be
honest with you.
>> Because your head is not on
the chopping block, or what?
>> Huh? Is my head on the
chopping block?
>> I said it's not on the
chopping block, so you're just
chilling?
>> I'm not thinking about it.
I mean, dude, you know what?
if I do go home tonight, then I
go home.
>> But you know, Brandon's head
is on the chopping block.
>> I definitely wouldn't let
Brandon go home.
>> That is whose head is on the
chopping block today.
>> Well, I know mine is too.
>> Well, you, you say that but
you know Brandon's head is on
the chopping block.
>> Well, you're telling me it
is.
>> You know it is.
>> I know mine is, too.
>> I have been honest this whole
game, told everybody what is up
and you can't even tell me who
are you sending home.
If you think you'd like to see
me go home, then just say it.
>> No.
>> We are all good farm boys so
if you got to say something,
say something.
>> Are you serious, man?
>> I guess they could afford to
lose one guy.
They're still gonna have us
outnumbered.
>> I'll be damned, man, if it
works out like that.
I'm going to crap my pants if it
>> I bet you I'm better at
crushing corn than you are.
>> Is that a challenge?
>> I just had this, you know, I
have been mentally prepared for
going home.
I have been thinking about like,
oh, man, going home, 21 days,
three weeks.
It was a good run, and you know,
getting prepared.
And now this comes by.
(thunder rumbling)
>> Finding that immunity idol
would be awesome.
But you don't know if you over-
looked it.
If you're not looking in the
right spot.
I mean, I could search out here
all day long and not find the
damn thing.
Hell, it's only six inches big,
and I don't even know what color
it looks like.
I guess really I'm hoping that
this one deal goes through and
uh, Jamie gets booted off rather
than... not myself.
People have been saying that
the whole time, like, "This
is Survivor."
Things get pushed around, it
will change.
Something will happen.
And something is starting to
happen.
>> If we do what's right, we
vote for Jamie.
If we do what's right.
Integrity and what's right.
There are five voting against
him, that's numbers.
>> Yeah, but then like,
you know, where does that leave
us?
>> Still on top, because then
there's nine.
>> Cindy, hey, do whatever you
need to do, you know what I
mean?
It's your thing.
>> But do what you need to do.
>> I don't know. I don't know
what to do.
It's really difficult.
I told the numbers of six, that,
you know, I'm voting for Brandon
because that is what we decided.
But my heart tells me to vote
for Jamie because I think
Brandon deserves to be here more
than Jamie.
But this game is not about who
you care the most about because
at some point you have to get
rid of everybody if you are
going to win.
So it is really very difficult.
I won't know until I write the
name down on the paper.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's events, a lot going on
out there.
Some people choosing to eat,
some taking part in the
challenge.
Rafe, were you are surprised
when Jamie said "Judd's up there
to protect our lead," implying
he's up there to protect this
alliance.
>> For me it was hard to hear
the comments Jamie was making,
just because I didn't want it to
become something like us versus
them or six versus four or
anything like that.
Which I guess was a little bit
naive in the game of Survivor.
This is a game about numbers.
But this is also a game about
respecting each other and, like,
I get really frustrated when we
don't do that.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, where does
it sit with you?
>> I just thought that was just
no class.
I mean, for somebody to sit
there and say, you know, "Go
Judd, whoo-whoo."
I'm just like that is just no
class.
I mean yeah, it's 6-4, whatever,
I know that.
That was just no class.
>> I have class.
So he can think what he wants to
think.
I'm the bigger man.
>> Man, just shut up, dude, I
mean, God.
>> Bobby Jon, I think no class
is when you have a chance for
immunity but you knew you had
the numbers so you didn't even
ask for it.
You thought you were too good to
>> 'Cause I knew that night I
was safe and I am an adult.
>> Try and let the people battle
for it who need it.
>> Brian needed immunity that
night.
He could have asked for it.
He didn't get it and I could
have gone home.
And Jeff was sitting right
there.
>> You weren't trying to save
Brian, though.
>> I don't even know what you
are saying, man.
are saying, but...
>> Stop. Stop.
>> I will let you have what you
want to have.
>> Okay, okay.
>> No one says I have no class.
You know, that is just
disrespectful.
I didn't disrespect him like
that.
I'm sorry I didn't play in that
game today, but we we'll see who
the bigger man is on the field.
(Bobby Jon scoffs)
>> PROBST: Cindy, why were you
in the challenge today?
You seem to be a part of this
magic six.
>> For me, I can eat when I get
home.
But I'll never have the chance
to do what I'm doing here ever
again.
And I'm going to do it as hard
as I can.
And yeah, it kind of hurt my
feelings a little bit, made me
feel like this group of six
people didn't have the faith in
me that they have in Judd.
But I stood there for an hour
just as long as Judd did.
I did everything I possibly
could, you know.
It makes things run through your
head like, "Well, then, who am
I, just standing here for the
heck of it?"
I'm an idiot for standing here?
>> PROBST: Gary, is it fair to
say that the six people fighting
for immunity today deserve to
stay in this game more than the
four who chose to eat?
>> You know, my hope would be
that everybody votes their heart
and not their mind.
Because at day 21 your mind can
play tricks on you.
But when you leave this game and
39 days are over, your heart is
going to be one that's gonna
tell you what's right and wrong.
>> PROBST: Cindy, at this
point in the game, what do you
base your vote on?
Is it as Gary said, heart and
morality and who deserves it, or
is it "As long as it ain't me"?
>> I think spending the time
that we spend with people out
here and getting to know people
and the level that you do, that
your morals and your heart
definitely come into play a
great deal.
It's impossible to block it out
if you even have a heart.
So it definitely comes into play
when you are making a decision.
It does for me.
>> PROBST: Okay, before we get
to the vote, an immunity idol
was hidden at your camp.
If anybody has found that and
you want to use it, now is the
time to present it.
Okay.
Either nobody has found the idol
or they just don't want to
reveal it at this time.
Gary has individual immunity,
he's the only one you cannot
vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Judd, you're up.
>> I have the utmost respect for
you.
We bled together and we fought
together, you are a good man.
I'm sorry you had to go.
>> You talk about having
Southern pride.
Well, part of having Southern
pride is being a Southern
gentleman.
And no, you don't have any class
at all.
>> PROBST: I will go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote, Brandon.
Brandon, two votes Brandon.
Jamie.
Two votes Brandon, one vote
Two votes Brandon, two votes
Jamie.
Brandon.
That's three votes Brandon,
two votes Jamie.
Jamie.
We're tied three votes each.
Brandon.
That's four votes Brandon,
three votes Jamie.
Jamie.
Tied again.
Four votes Brandon,
four votes Jamie.
Brandon.
Five votes Brandon,
Four votes Jamie.
One vote left.
Ninth person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala, Brandon.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> You're the sister I never
had.
>> PROBST: Brandon, the tribe
has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Well, you have made
it to the Final Nine.
Two of you will make it to the
Final Two, the other seven will
make up the jury.
18 days left, a lot can happen.
One thing is certain, everything
you've done up until now and
everything you do from here on
out matters.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on Survivor
the battle continues.
>> Jamie's about that far from
hitting my breaking point.
>> PROBST: The search for the
hidden immunity idol
intensifies.
>> I'm going to pull out
everything I can to try and get
as far as I can.
>> PROBST: And one Survivor has
lost all respect.
>> Judd threw up in the shelter.
>> It's all a blur to me, man.
>> I played the game I came out
here to play, and I think
I played a pretty good game,
a pretty straight up game.
I wasn't always all about the
money.
I was playing the game for
myself.
You can take me out of this game
before you take my pride.
And I think I did a pretty good
job of that.
I think I can walk away from
this and, you know, take