>> JEFF PROBST: We're in Patan
in northern Guatemala surrounded
by ruins that are thousands of
years old.
Hidden deep in the jungle these
ruins are a monument to a once
powerful and sophisticated
civilization, the Maya.
Best-known for their advanced
celestial knowledge and uncanny
ability to calculate time, the
Maya culture thrived and then
mysteriously vanished.
Today, these jungles are home to
exotic and dangerous wildlife--
jaguars, poisonous snakes and
crocodiles that lurk in every
body of water.
It is an unforgiving
environment, where extreme
temperatures, high humidity
and torrential rainstorms
bring even the strongest
to their knees.
It is here that a group of
Americans have already begun the
adventure of a lifetime.
They have been divided into two
tribes, hiking to a destination
unknown with no idea of the
surprise that awaits them.
( howling )
It is the ultimate challenge.
18 strangers forced to work
together to create a new society
while battling the elements and
each other.
They must learn to adapt, or
they will be voted out of the
tribe.
In the end, only one will remain
to claim the $1 million prize.
39 days, 18 people, one
survivor.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Welcome to Survivor:
Guatemala.
You are standing in the ruins of
an ancient Mayan civilization
that is literally thousands of
years old.
For the next 39 days, you will
live amongst these ruins like
the Maya did.
Already been divided into two
tribes.
Nakum, wearing yellow.
In the back, you'll hold that.
Yaxha, wearing blue.
All right.
You'll both live at separate
camps.
Waiting for you at each camp
will be a few items used by the
Maya that will help you live
like the Maya did.
In addition to the things
waiting for you at camp, each
tribe will have one other tool
to aid you in this game.
Come on out.
( laughter )
( applause )
>> PROBST: I'm sure you guys
recognize Bobby Jon and
Stephenie from Survivor:
Palau.
Come on down.
These are two proven Survivor
players.
They've been through this
experience.
They know how to make fire.
They know how to source food.
They know how to build shelter.
With Stephenie, you have
arguably the strongest woman to
ever play this game, and
somebody who has proven she will
not quit.
With Bobby Jon, a strong
competitor at challenges
and in day-to-day camp living,
arguably the hardest-working
survivor ever.
>> What's up, guys?
>> PROBST: Stephenie is a member
of Yaxha.
( cheering )
>> I'm, like, in love with
Stephenie.
So, when I found out she was on
our team.
I was, like, "Oh, we're winning.
We got Stephenie, like, we're
good to go.
>> I cried.
I couldn't help but just cry.
She is such an inspiration.
>> Like all the girls are crying
when they saw Stephenie because
that's their hero.
I didn't shed a tear when I saw
her.
I was, like, "How am I going to
win $1 million, now that she's
here?"
>> Bobby Jon is a member of
Nakum.
( cheering )
>> We're really happy with Bobby
Jon on our tribe.
A man is just stronger than a
woman is and it makes it easy on
the eyes around the tribe, so
that's always a plus.
>> We were just thrilled to have
Bobby Jon because he's not going
to quit for anything, and he's
not going to disappoint somebody
on his tribe.
>> Bobby Jon is a tough worker
supposedly, so I hear.
I don't know.
We'll have to see, but, you
know, kind of a little bit dumb,
I guess you'd say.
>> Let me be perfectly clear
about this.
Stephenie and Bobby Jon are
full-fledged members of your
tribes.
They are players in this game.
You can use their backbone and
their experience to further your
own tribe or, if you think it
makes more sense, they're
certainly an easy first vote off
the first time you go to Tribal
Council.
All right.
Let's get to your first
challenge.
It is for reward.
It is a grueling 11-mile race
through the jungles of
Guatemala.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: It is going to be
long.
It is going to be hot.
There are poisonous snakes at
every corner.
There are crocodiles in every
body of water out here.
The trek finishes at the better
of the two camps.
The winning tribe claims the
right to the better camp, which
is also a natural Maya ruin.
They also get flint to make
fire, critical in this game,
right, Steph?
>> Right.
>> PROBST: Losers, you get the
lesser of the two camps.
You get no flint.
You got no fire.
You're off to a real rough
start.
Big stakes right away.
Pace yourself.
This is a marathon, not a
sprint.
You'll know you're near the
finish when you see your tribe
canoes.
Yaxha you will head up these
steps, around the path to the
right.
Nakum, you will head up these
steps, follow the path to the
left.
Waiting for you is a compass and
a map.
You'll also find water, fruit,
bags of corn.
It is up to you to decide how
much you want to carry with you.
I'll be waiting for you at the
finish.
Survivor: Guatemala is set to
begin.
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> When we first saw all the
fruit, all the water, we had to
decide what stuff we were gonna
carry with us.
It was kind of a little bit of
mass chaos.
>> Grab the bananas.
>> Somebody bust something open
and let's eat it while we're
here.
>> None of us have ever talked
before, so to figure out a
strategy on the spur of the
moment was a little tough.
>> Take a thing of corn.
>> I say we just go ahead and
start going, guys.
>> Let's go, guys.
>> Being a farmer and
everything, the last time I
hiked 11 miles was never, but,
uh, I took off after 'em, you
know-- yeehaw!
You know, ready to do this, man.
>> Oh, yeah. Feels good.
>> We'll get over there, man.
Just lay down, relax.
>> Yup.
>> Just hang out, sing some
songs.
Being back in Survivor, I was
glad to get a new start.
I felt like a million bucks at
the beginning of the race.
But we've got to make time
because I guarantee you, Miss
Stephenie is over there running
things, and she won't, she won't
take time.
You drop it, you leave it, you
go.
>> So one person in the water.
( overlapping voices )
>> No, I'm all right.
>> All right.
>> My main fear coming into the
game was that, yes, I may be
sort of like a tool 'cause I-I
have experience and I kind of
came in almost like an outsider.
But Yaxha welcomed me with open
arms.
>> Stephenie, you're the reason
why I'm here.
>> Oh, stop it.
>> Totally awesome.
>> But I still have that
nervousness that maybe they will
see me as too threatening or
maybe I'm not as spectacular as
they thought I would have been.
And maybe they do want to just
get rid of me.
>> Let's roll.
>> Let's go.
>> How do you pronounce our
tribe?
>> Yasha.
( howling )
>> "Use your compass to walk a
straight line until you hit the
old archeological road."
>> One and a quarter mile.
>> Oh, man.
>> We're gonna have a leader?
>> Why don't we leapfrog?
Go right for that big, tallest
tree right to your left, uh,
Blake...
>> Might need to come this way.
>> Come to your right, Blake.
>> What?
>> Come to your right.
The jungle, you know, you
can't move ten feet straight
ahead.
So, I put one of my tribesmen
I'd have him walk up to a point
on my compass.
And then we all walked to him,
and it was slow going.
Can we see him, anybody?
>> Um...
>> No.
>> Oh, I see him, I see him.
Okay.
All right, stay right there.
Most of the people couldn't
read a compass.
I've done it before, you know,
in the Marine Corps, but you can
walk in circles in that stuff if
you don't do it right.
>> Is everybody here?
>> Yeah.
>> It's going to get too thick
to do this.
>> Well, it's gonna get too dark
to do it, is what's gonna
happen.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, weave to your left.
>> Right here?
>> Yup.
>> To the large mound?
>> Check it out.
>> "Travel left past the large
mounds."
>> Hey, uh, Gary, you going the
right way?
>> Yeah, you're right.
>> That way. We go left.
>> Go right around 'em.
>> No question, straight south.
Go.
>> On Survivor, the leader
always gets friggin' voted out
first if someone steps up and
takes leadership.
And it was clear at the
beginning that Gary was our
leader.
He's taller than everyone.
He's gray-haired.
He was our leader, no question.
>> West through...
>> No, we need to turn right
now, north.
>> Gary, what do you do?
>> All right.
>> You know, they've asked me
what I do, so I told them I was
a landscaper.
15 years ago, I was in the
NFL for 11 years.
My real name is Gary Hogeboom,
but I don't think anybody needs
to know that, because I'd be
voted off immediately.
I don't see any markers.
What do you think?
If somebody does recognize me,
I'm just gonna say that's not
me.
I'm Gary Hawkins.
>> Let's go, guys.
>> We're going... we're going
north.
>> Gary and I, very early on, we
both took a compass and we were
the navigators, basically.
Make sure we're going the
right way.
It's hard in an 11-and-a-half
mile hike to not get lost or,
you know, miss a trail or
whatever.
We going the right way?
>> What's the compass say?
>> Well, this is... this is
where we thought we were just
right now?
>> Yep.
>> I think that's leading us to
nowhere.
>> Well, that's not so good.
>> We made some bad decisions,
and, uh, I was the one with the
compass.
But, uh, oh, my gosh, you know,
how many young people we got
there?
Morgan, Brianna, Steph, Jamie,
Brian.
They're, you know, what are
they, 21, 22?
I don't want to be a leader, but
my paternal instincts will kick
in with these kids.
Keep up those spirits.
>> Watch out.
It's very thorny.
Watch where you step.
( yells )
>> Got it there?
>> I'm stuck.
>> Watch out for this tree.
>> Here I come, baby, coming
full force at you.
11 miles in a jungle is
absolutely insane.
I mean, you're just sitting
there fighting things coming
down, and just getting to where
you want to go, and just...
It was, by far, one of the
toughest things I've ever
done in my life.
I'm just a freaking doorman
from New York, man.
I never even went camping.
>> I hope this is over really
soon, because... it's getting
dark awfully fast.
Bobby Jon, right past that.
Look at, look at that... tall...
>> Yeah.
>> See that?
>> Got it.
>> Go down, go right down there.
>> Okay.
>> Even if we're off a little
bit.
>> Stay a little to the left,
Bobby Jon.
( yelling )
>> Oh!
>> That's got thorns in it.
>> Oh, no.
>> Great.
>> ...in the shoulders...
>> We're going through the
jungle, and one of these trees
that have briers that look like
spikes, actually broke on
Blake's shoulder.
>> The branch, I mean, it didn't
even, like, deflect.
Like it cracked over my
shoulder.
God.
>> A porcupine tree.
>> Whoa.
>> I think it was just one of
those reality checks that, you
know, a scorpion could sting
you, a snake could bite you.
It's any one of us.
>> I've got two in here.
>> All right, get after her,
girl.
>> Hold on.
I'm a nurse by trade.
I've been a nurse for 25
years, most of it trauma.
Does that hurt?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Okay, it's out.
That really took him down a
couple notches.
Do you feel any more?
>> No. I don't.
>> Okay, stand up.
>> Watch these trees right here.
Trees right there...
>> Hold up just a second.
>> Let us know when you're
ready.
>> Porcupine tree.
>> Whoa.
( sighs )
>> We're going the right
direction.
We've just got to try to speed
it up.
Catch up, anyway.
>> This is all trees.
It's so dark.
>> Guys, wait. Wait, please.
>> You want to stop?
>> What's right here?
>> It's kind of a clearing right
here.
>> Right here.
Pick a spot right here.
>> Yeah, yeah, we should stop.
>> We really didn't want to
stop.
You know, it just got so dark
and we are in thick jungle.
>> Don't cut yourself when you
go down on the ground with your
hand.
>> Nakum is probably right in
front of us.
We'll get up as soon as the sun
starts to rise, and we will
hopefully pull ahead.
I mean, this...
I'm not starting off...
in Guatemala on the losing team,
terrible.
( howling )
( retching )
>> Yeah.
Let me just catch my breath.
>> Okay.
>> You know what?
Why don't we get some palm
fronds to put down so he can lay
down?
>> Got my shoulder knocked real
good back there, and it's just
slowing me down.
The thorns went deep inside,
and... I think I'm a little
dehydrated, my body...
my hand is a little
tingly and...
I'll be all right.
( retching )
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Oh, son of a bitch.
>> Blake, we're really worried
about him.
The problem is his shoulder hurt
so badly, I think it's causing a
pain response to make him sick
to his stomach.
>> Thanks, Margaret, I
appreciate it.
>> We're hoping that he'll feel
better in the morning.
( retching )
( howling )
>> As soon as the sun came up,
we started hearing some noises.
It reminded me of Predator.
( howling )
I looked up, I saw a monkey
going from tree to tree.
And I'm, like, "Oh, my God.
I can't believe this."
( howling continues )
>> Hey, guys, if we want to beat
Nakum, I think we should start
getting up and going.
>> In ten minutes, it'll be
better.
>> Well, in ten minutes, they
might be going, and they're
already ahead of us.
I wanted to get a move on
because I knew that Nakum would
start at daybreak.
People were a little cranky, but
they knew that I was right and
we did need to go.
>> Let's go.
>> We actually found the other
tribe, Nakum, which was great,
because we were... last we knew,
we were hours behind them.
>> Yaxha, come on.
>> Let's go, guys.
We got to move.
>> Come on, guys.
>> Meeting up in the jungle with
the other tribe took quite a bit
of air out of our balloon.
>> The other team's on our back.
>> Let's go.
>> Hey, we got road!
>> Yeah, baby!
>> Everybody coming?
We came out of the jungle
into a more open trail before
the other tribe, but they were
still right behind us.
>> Come on, Yaxha!
>> We cannot lose this entire
tribe.
>> We-We just wanted to get them
off our tails.
>> Come on, pick it up.
They're behind us.
It was like the movie Sea
Biscuit, when he sees his
competition and he kicks it in.
I was just like...
I felt like I couldn't put one
foot in front of me and all of a
sudden I'm running down this
trail in the muck.
>> We need to get right on their
ass, if not pass them.
>> Yeah. Come on, guys.
Push it.
We had Nakum.
They were right in front of us,
and then, all of a sudden, a
couple people, unfortunately, on
our tribe-- like Lydia and Amy,
who aren't as fit-- they were
kind of like lagging behind.
And it's a challenge that
you're only as strong as your
weakest link and we had to wait
for everybody till we could move
on.
And we had them.
They were right in front of us,
and we lost them completely.
>> You want me to take that
flag?
All right. Ready?
We're gonna do a slow jog
together.
Ready?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's go, Nakum.
>> Come on, Bobby Jon.
>> All of a sudden, I just got
cold as ice and my body
severely, severely cramped.
>> My hand's cramping.
>> Okay.
>> I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
>> Okay, it's okay.
>> Get some water, please.
>> All right now.
>> Bobby Jon started getting
really bad cramps.
It's dehydration, overexertion.
He carried two bags of corn the
entire trek.
So, here comes Margaret the
nurse lady, and she just talked
him through it.
>> All right, I'm-I'm good.
>> Keep this leg...
Bend this leg up first.
>> Here you go, Bobby.
Okay.
>> I have to try. Let's go.
>> Okay.
>> I think people were
surprised, because this guy's in
better shape probably for this
and knows what to expect more
than anybody and he's going down
early.
I don't think anybody expected
that.
>> Okay?
>> Can we move faster, guys?
Can we move faster?
>> Yup.
>> All right.
>> How is everyone feeling?
>> You guys, everybody doing
okay?
>> Everybody good?
>> Yep.
>> Because we have a chance to
catch up with 'em.
>> Okay. Good job.
>> Hey, do I see water?
>> Guys, we're almost there.
>> Ow! Ow!
>> When I saw the boats, by that
time I was just absolutely
winded, but I knew that's the
light at the end of the tunnel.
Here we go.
>> "Paddle your canoe west-
southwest to the first wooden
pier, which is attached to the
stone steps.
Follow the path up to the Maya
ruins to the winners' camp."
>> All right, let's go, guys.
>> Everybody in, pile in.
When the other team shows up,
it's gonna be a race to the
finish.
>> Come on, guys, paddle.
Get it together.
>> Here they are.
>> There they are.
>> Guys, we have to pick it up.
Just stay hard.
Slow but hard.
( shouting )
>> Emerging from the jungle, we
see Nakum right there in the
middle of the lake.
We were so much closer than we
thought we were.
And we just booked it to our
canoe.
We knew we had caught up.
It was a huge morale booster.
>> Stroke.
>> Come on, guys.
>> I think we need to get in a
rhythm.
>> Never give up, guys, come on.
Stroke.
( indistinct voices )
>> As close to the dock as
possible.
>> Get up there, Judd, and pull
us up.
>> Ah!
>> We get to the dock, and old
Judd jumps out of the boat.
He had a premature evacuation.
And he gets into this mud that's
almost like quicksand.
>> It's hard to get out of, man.
( indistinct voices )
>> Stroke. Keep paddling.
Don't stop.
You got it.
>> Come on, babe, let's go.
Come on!
>> Bobby Jon's got this.
>> I'm trying, dawg.
>> Okay, left side, left side,
come on.
>> Pull.
>> We're almost there, guys.
Come on.
>> Pull.
>> Oh, my God.
Getting out of the boat was a
nightmare.
I knew it was dehydration, but
I've never felt that type of
pain before.
I knew the other tribe was
definitely on our tail, so it's
kind of like you got to suck it
up.
But it was just tough.
>> They're right there.
Everyone give it.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Yeah!
( whooping )
>> PROBST: Welcome, Nakum.
( cheering )
Congratulations.
>> Nakum!
>> PROBST: Nicely done, guys.
( groaning )
>> PROBST: So, 11 miles, 24-hour
trek, you guys definitely earned
the better of the two camps.
Here is your tribe flag.
More important, who wants it?
Margaret, flint.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Take care of that.
Congratulations.
Good luck.
>> Awesome.
Still got some spring
in those steps.
>> Nice job there, guys.
Nice job, nice job.
>> PROBST: Don't get too
comfortable, you're not staying.
This is not your camp.
I think it's fair to say, given
that this was an 11-mile trek
through the jungle, a very close
finish, but in Survivor, close
gets you nothing.
This is where you will not be
living.
This is a map to where you will
be living.
Who wants it?
Okay, you've got more paddling
to do.
Here's your tribe flag.
All right, guys.
Take your stuff and go.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Bye.
>> See you later.
>> You know, we lost, but we...
I thought we kicked butt.
I thought we did really well.
I think it was the most
difficult challenge the game's
ever had.
>> So we leave the ruins, we
leave the winners, and we're
bummed, because, you know, it's
taken us 24 hours to get there
and we worked really hard.
>> So we've got to go down
there, you guys?
>> Yes.
>> It kind of stunk for us,
because, you know, we get all
the way there, we lose, so we
had to paddle all the way across
the lake to get to our camp.
So it was a lot of extra work.
>> You want to check out where
the camp is before we carry all
this crap?
>> We're just gonna leave it on
the dock.
Let's just unload as much as
we can.
>> Come on, Yaxha, I know we're
tired.
>> Let's go, you guys.
>> All right.
>> When we started walking up to
our camp, we didn't know what to
expect.
>> I see it, you guys.
>> Our home.
>> Whoa, what's up with the
pots?
>> That's for the corn.
>> That's a perfect one to cook
tortillas.
>> We finally got to camp.
It sucks we don't have water,
but we're making do.
>> So, maybe we should talk
about shelter and where we want
to build it and how we want to
build it.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, this isn't bad.
>> Let's go.
>> Making a lean-to'd be
awesome, 'cause you know, water
runs off.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, actually this is an
incline, guys.
>> I'm just gonna shove 'em
through.
You just got to pull them
where you can.
>> I'll build you your dream
home.
>> I am so psyched.
Finally I'm on a tribe that's
got as much heart and
determination as me.
>> Yeah, see how good that is?
>> Good job. You got it.
It's under.
>> Yes.
>> We were dead tired, but all
we had left was, you know, this
Yaxha spirit, like, "We can do
this and we don't care if we're
coming in second.
We're giving it everything we
have."
>> That's going to be good, I
think.
( retching )
>> How you doing, Blake?
( panting )
( retching )
>> Breathe through your nose,
Blake.
The combination of going through
the jungle and trying to get
here has dehydrated so many of
us.
( retching )
>> Judd, you okay back there?
Judd's down.
( groans )
Blake's down.
( retching )
Jim's not doing well, and
Bobby Jon's down.
They're all vomiting.
They're all cramped up.
>> Bobby Jon.
Bobby Jon.
>> Huh?
>> Oh, his eyes are rolling
back.
Bobby Jon?
Come on, Bobby Jon.
Focus.
Slow.
Breathe through your nose.
Bobby Jon?
Bobby?
Stay with me.
Yup.
Bobby Jon, stay with me.
Okay, okay.
Let's just rub your legs here.
Okay.
Just keep them up like that.
Keep them up like that.
Just a little. Little tiny...
>> He'll throw it up, if...
>> I started having the shakes,
just was cramping everywhere
that I never knew I could cramp.
If it wouldn't have been for
Margaret, I really felt I might
have had a seizure.
It was a nightmare.
Palau was recess compared to
Guatemala.
( retching )
>> Blake good?
>> We are messed up!
>> These big, strong guys,
strong as oxes, and they are all
down.
( groans )
>> What do we need to do?
>> We need to just make rounds
with them and give them water.
That's all we need to do.
The girls are holding up
remarkably well.
>> Big enough so you don't get
sick again.
>> But we didn't expect the guys
to go down so quickly.
Don't get up, lay down.
Stay down, stay down.
>> It was a bittersweet victory
because we won.
We got there first.
We got the fire and the best
camp, but some of us were in
such bad shape, you're thinking
if we lose 'em, it's not even
worth having all this.
>> Oh, my God, it's an oar.
>> Let's go back, let's go back.
>> "Your first two days were
grueling, but now is no time to
rest.
You've come too far to lose it
now.
This will put you to the test.
You'll be competing like the
Maya.
This is more than just a game.
Fail to pull your weight today,
and be the first to lose your
flame."
>> Okay, here's what I've
learned from my thing...
Uh, for me, this is really
exciting to have another chance
at immunity and possibly come
out with a victory.
Usually the person who steers
is one of the strongest, 'cause
they row both sides and steer.
But also it's a lot of pressure,
because if we lose this
challenge I'm going to be really
down.
>> Tree mail.
>> It says we're going to be
competing like the Maya.
>> Definitely our tribe not
being in tip-top shape right now
is a concern.
>> We're all staying here
tonight.
>> Yeah.
>> Nobody is going home.
>> I think the girls
right now are the strongest
physically, but if our guys
go up for this challenge
and turn it on like no other
then we're definitely going to
have a good day today.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to your first immunity
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Let me show you what
you're playing for.
This is it.
( applause )
The game revolves around
immunity.
As long as you have it in your
possession, whether as a tribe
or an individual, you're safe.
If not, you're in danger of
going home.
Okay, let's get to the
challenge.
It is based on the method that
the Maya used for transporting
materials to build their
pyramids.
Here's how it works.
On my "go" all nine of you will
paddle out in a boat, around a
buoy, grab a torch, come back.
Once you reach the shore, you'll
drag your boat up the beach and
attach it to a rope.
At that point, four people will
race up the hill and begin
pulling on that rope.
As you pull, you'll move the
boat over a series of rolling
logs.
This is how the Maya did it.
Every time you clear a log, four
other people will take that back
log and move it to the front.
That'll keep the momentum
going.
That leaves one person left.
Their sole responsibility is
carrying that torch.
Once the boat crosses the finish
line the person with the torch
lights the fire.
The first tribe to get their
flame lit wins immunity.
For the losers, Tribal Council.
First person will be voted out.
Yaxha, you still need fire.
Win this challenge,
you get your fire.
>> We're going to get it, guys.
>> PROBST: Pick your spots.
Wait for my "go."
Here we go.
For immunity, Survivors ready.
Go.
>> Let's go, guys. Let's go.
>> Come on, guys.
( indistinct voices )
>> PROBST: Both tribes out
pretty even.
>> Come on. Dig.
>> Come on...
>> Come on, you guys.
( shouting )
>> PROBST: Dead-even at the
buoy; Yaxha has their torch.
They're making their turn.
Gonna have a collision.
>> Nakum struggling at the
buoy, trying to get their torch.
Yaxha working well.
Navigates through.
Chance to take the lead.
>> Come on, Yaxha.
>> Row! Row! Row!
>> Stroke!
( indistinct shouting )
>> PROBST: Very tight coming
back to the beach.
Yaxha getting off their boat.
Nakum off their boat.
Going to take strength
and working together.
Got to work together.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Nakum has their rope
attached.
Bobby Jon, Brandon, Blake, Judd.
>> He's had enough.
>> PROBST: Jim, going to stay
back with the women.
Yaxha right behind with Jamie,
Gary, Brian, Rafe.
>> Go, guys!
>> Go, go, go.
>> One, two, three.
>> Push.
>> One...
>> One, two...
>> Ow!
My foot, my foot is under the
log.
>> Stop, go back.
>> PROBST: Stephenie's foot is
caught under a log.
She's got it free, but now Nakum
is back ahead.
A lot of work pulling this heavy
boat.
Yaxha is really digging in.
They've closed the gap.
Both tribes are even.
>> Push wit your legs.
One, two, three, four.
>> PROBST: Yaxha now with a bit
a lead.
Margaret took one in the gut.
>> Hold up, hold up.
>> PROBST: Nakum falling behind.
( groans )
Danni is caught under a log.
>> It's on my foot! Go back.
>> PROBST: Cindy's stuck.
A log on her foot.
>> Let's go, girls.
We need you...
>> Hold on.
>> PROBST: Nakum really
struggling now.
>> Let's go.
One, two, three, four.
( grunts )
>> PROBST: Yaxha has taken a big
league.
>> Pull!
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Nakum not giving up.
( collective shout )
Yaxha very close to the finish.
>> Let's go, Yaxha!
>> PROBST: Yaxha has crossed the
finish line.
Lydia has got to light the fire.
Yaxha wins immunity.
( cheering and shouting )
>> One, two, three, Yaxha!
>> We've got immunity, baby.
>> PROBST: Yaxha, first immunity
goes to you.
Along with something just as
important right now for you
guys-- flint to make fire.
For the first time, Steph, there
will be a Tribal Council
in which you've been a part of
Survivor that you won't be at.
( cheering and whistling )
Nakum, Tribal Council tonight.
Sadly, somebody will be the
first person voted out.
Head on back.
>> Losing the immunity
challenge today was really
tough.
We worked our way up from having
four guys who were badly down
yesterday.
The heat sapped us.
It was... it was excruciating.
>> God...
>> It popped right when...
when we picked the canoe up.
I thought everybody else was
lifting, and I was lifting by
myself.
It just went "pop."
>> Lifted that bad boy up like I
never lifted anything before in
my life.
>> Yeah, and so was I.
We knew this challenge ought to
be something brutal, and it
turned out that it was.
My left bicep literally snapped.
>> Let me get a cloth for it and
see if I can put it behind us.
( groans )
>> I'm really starting to adapt
to this jungle.
Jungle Judd.
What about you?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You enjoying the jungle
life?
>> I'm doing good.
Oh, I'm surprised. I felt...
I felt all right after the 11
miles.
Since we lost the
immunity challenge we know one
of us has to leave and none of
us deserves to go.
I mean, I definitely don't want
any of the women to go yet and
we've really shown that we have
the endurance for 40 days.
I mean, I feel fine, and we...
I mean, all of us were able to
stick through it really hard
yesterday and do a ton of
work.
And Brandon hasn't sat down yet.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I don't know.
I mean, Bobby Jon was the
sickest yesterday, by far.
I mean, his eyes were rolling
back in his head.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> He was the worst off.
( howling )
>> I need some of that water,
man.
>> Here.
I don't know what's
going to happen at Tribal,
but we might send off one of
these crippled, you know,
broke-down guys.
I mean, I'm having doubts if
half of these people are even
going to make it.
Blake, he's all crippled up and
his shoulder is like killing
him.
He's kind of, you know, still
throwing up, and he's getting
cramps really bad, and he's the
one I'm most concerned about.
>> You got to take a sip.
You still can dehydrate out
here, okay?
It has some lemon in it.
When there's at least three
people absolutely flat on their
back-- a third of your team is
out-- you know, strategizing is
a little bit tough.
I really like Bobby Jon.
I think he's a strong player.
Jim, he's a great guy.
He's got a lot of offer.
I-I like Blake.
In this tribe, they are all
great people, but it's-it's all
about who can help carry this
team forward.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch
and approach the flame,
because in this game
fire represents your life.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
Take a seat.
Before we get started, we have
to acknowledge where we are.
You're in the midst of the North
Acropolis.
These are authentic Maya ruins,
and thousands of years ago this
is a spot where leaders would
decide the fate of their people.
Couldn't be a more fitting spot
for Tribal Council.
All right, so let's get to it.
This is the toughest beginning
to any Survivor we've ever had.
Blake, immediately your head
just went down like, "Yeah, I
know."
>> It's been pretty tough, Jeff.
That first day, you know, Bobby
Jon, myself and Jim and Judd, we
were cramping all up and down
and sick to our stomachs and
couldn't keep anything down and
dehydration, and...
it was definitely a hard start
to this adventure, for sure.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, how about
for you?
>> I don't like getting beat
down like that this early in the
game.
I've never had that happen to me
before.
I mean, I know I could be saying
sayonara tonight.
I hope... I hope to God I don't
have to.
I mean, not many people get
two chances to win a million
bucks.
>> Danni, looking at this group,
you've got a lot of young,
strong guys.
You had you to be a little
surprised to see four of your
five guys on their back.
>> Well, I was a-a little
surprised, but I think a lot of
times guys have more physical
strength, but women tend to have
a little more endurance.
Maybe that played a part of it,
but also, they were carrying at
the beginning, a lot of the load
and so they were throwing up and
getting sick and that's going to
happen.
That's just part of the game.
>> PROBST: Judd, you come out.
If I'm looking, I'm thinking,
"All right, I've got to rely on
Judd," especially through this
trek and some of these physical
challenges and you're on your
back.
You have to be thinking "Am I in
trouble?"
>> Not at all.
I mean, I was... I was only on
my back for like an hour at the
most.
I mean, I got right over it.
I puked and I got up and I went
to do what I had to do, man.
I mean, I don't know what to
tell you.
I'm ready to do a back flip if
you want me to.
I mean, I feel great.
>> PROBST: Wow, I just asked a
simple question.
( laughing )
Let's talk about today's
challenge.
Jim, so what is up with your
arm?
'Cause you've made a
homemade sling over there.
>> Yeah, first thing out of the
chute when we picked up the
boat, I grabbed it with my left
arm.
And I was under the impression
everybody else had ahold of it.
Sure didn't, and it just tore
that bicep muscle.
>> PROBST: When did you know?
Did you know instantly?
>> I knew when I picked it up.
It popped. I heard it pop.
I was 50%, but I'm not blaming
it on my arm.
When you don't have everybody at
100%, it's going to hurt.
It's going to hurt the-the
tribe.
>> PROBST: Margaret, three days
in, a lot of people have taken
lumps.
What thoughts have you been
thinking about in terms of "What
do we need to do in this game?"
>> I mean, all of us are very
worried about how to pace our
team to put us in the winning
position for both the rewards
and not to be here at Tribal
Council, so we are trying to
realign our priorities and
conserve energy, keep ourself
healthy and think straight, so
that's what I see coming.
>> PROBST: Okay.
It is time to vote.
Blake, you're up.
>> One of the toughest dudes I
know.
>> I know you're a fighter, and
I know you don't want to quit,
but I have to make this vote
thinking of the team for long
term.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Jim.
Jim. Two votes Jim.
That's three votes Jim.
Jim.
Four votes Jim.
First person voted out
of Survivor: Guatemala -- Jim.
That's five. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Jim, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Thanks, Jim.
>> Thanks, Jimbo.
>> PROBST: You have 36 more days
out here, and it seems like the
dilemma for this tribe is how to
give it your all without
destroying yourself in the
process.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: Yaxha takes
desperate measures for food.
>> You want to eat ants?
>> We need protein.
>> I'm not going to be eating
ants.
>> PROBST: The challenges get
tougher...
( yelling )
...and Blake hits rock bottom.
>> I'm really, really worried
about Blake.
He's struggling to get breaths,
and something's not right.
>> Well, I'm not particularly
surprised by the outcome of all
this, you know, given the
difficulty of this game and, you
know, being an older guy.
I'm proud of what I did at my
age.
I'd like to motivate people to
get out and do things-- you
know, do something for yourself.
I don't blame the guys for
voting me out.
I wish them good luck, and, uh,