>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: Yaxha and Nakum
merged in the dead of night.
>> We have some new buffs for
you.
>> Merge, baby, merge.
>> PROBST: The old Yaxha members
felt outnumbered.
>> There's four of us from Yaxha
tribe and six of them from the
Nakum tribe.
And things aren't looking very
up.
>> PROBST: Tree mail brought
word of a small immunity idol
hidden nearby in the jungle.
>> "There is an individual
immunity idol in the woods."
>> "You can use it at any time
to save yourself.
You don't need to tell anyone
you have it, but if you're going
to use it, you must present it
before the vote."
>> PROBST: And the search was
on.
>> We got tree mail saying that
there's a little immunity idol
about this big in the jungle
that's this big.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Survivors chose
between competing for individual
immunity or partaking in a
feast.
If you participate in the
challenge, you don't eat.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Jamie made clear the
tribe divide as he harassed
Bobby Jon.
>> Brandon and Bobby Jon know
they have a chance of going home
tonight 'cause they're the best
two athletes in the group.
>> I thought we were one tribe.
>> You know we're not one tribe.
So why you saying that right
right now?
>> Because I can.
>> PROBST: In the tie-breaking
round, Gary took home individual
immunity.
Gary wins immunity.
>> PROBST: Back at camp, Jamie
revealed that Brandon's time was
up.
>> You say that, but you know
Brandon's head is on the
chopping block.
>> PROBST: But some of Jamie's
old allies were fed up with
him...
>> Dude, shut up, man, shut up,
man.
I can't listen to you right now.
>> PROBST: ...giving Brandon a
glimmer of hope.
>> People have been saying...
>> This is Survivor.
Things get switched around.
It'll change.
You know, something will happen,
and something's starting to
happen.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Bobby Jon and Jamie were once
again at each other's throats.
>> That's just no class.
>> No one says I have no class.
You know, that's just
disrespectful.
Man, just shut up, dude.
I mean, God!
>> PROBST: Okay, before we get
to the vote, the immunity idol
was hidden at your camp.
If anybody has found that, now
is the time to present it.
When no one produced the idol,
the votes were close between
Jamie and Brandon.
But, in the end, it was Brandon
who was sent home.
Brandon, the tribe has spoken.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> I don't know.
It's bull when you call... when
you say someone has no class.
You shouldn't judge another man.
You know?
>> Yeah, but just take some time
and, like, you know, don't
react.
Like, we're all making the jury,
and, like, let's just take
tonight and sleep.
>> I'm not, man.
>> You don't want to go to bed
angry, man.
That ain't a good thing to do,
bro.
>> I'm not angry.
My feelings are hurt.
>> I called Jamie out at Tribal
Council, and it really got to
him because he knows I told the
truth.
I mean, the kid showed no class
today, none, whatsoever.
>> Why did you say I have no
class?
>> Because at the time we were
competing and, you know, you're
rooting another person on that's
competing right beside them to
me, and I may have a wrong
opinion, and if I do, I'm sorry,
but it was, that's how it came
off to me, you know, hey.
(chuckles)
>> My action might have had no
class, but saying I have no
class is like calling me white
trash, Bobby Jon.
>> That was just because that's
how I felt at that moment today.
Tomorrow the sun comes up.
>> It broke my heart.
It did.
>> I'm sorry.
I don't mean to break anybody's
heart.
>> I don't think he was judging.
He wasn't judging you.
I think he was just saying at
that moment.
>> You're taking it a little too
personal, man.
>> I don't understand how this
wouldn't hurt y'all's feelings.
>> 'Cause... you know why?
Because this is competition, and
some things... you say things
when you don't mean it.
You just say it.
>> Are we cool?
>> I hate all the drama, but I'm
just straight up telling you.
>> Well, hey, speak your heart.
>> Hallelujah.
>> Jamie took it way too
personally.
I think he was just looking for
some kind of outlet for all the
emotion he was feeling, and the
way for him to do that was to
kind of blame Bobby Jon.
And if Jamie doesn't use this as
an experience to learn and
change from, then I'm going to
change up this game.
>> If I left tonight, I don't
know, God, what I would have
done.
I would be swimming in
depression.
(tapping)
>> Breakfast is ready.
Judd?
>> I'll pass on eating today,
man.
Other than the food, camp life
is great, man.
I mean, at this point of the
game, we're up in numbers, so, I
mean, we got 6-3 right now, so
the most vulnerable now is
Danni, Gary, and Bobby Jon.
And they know they are.
>> Exactly.
>> Listen, if it was the other
way around, they'd be doing the
same thing.
>> Mm-hmm.
(laughter)
>> Yeah.
It's got to be here somewhere.
Our ass depends on it.
>> I need that immunity idol
now.
I need it right now.
It's going to be tough.
Um, all I know from the clues is
that it's visible, but it's
going to be hard to find.
But that's the only chance I
have.
I'm on the chopping block.
There's pretty much nothing I
can do to budge the magical six
up there.
What do you do?
You just got to keep trying.
>> It's hopeless.
We can't find it anywhere.
Hopefully, we'll get some more
clues to where it might be.
But I'm just praying.
So maybe the Lord will lead me
to it.
>> In the NFL, we played
against Detroit one year, and we
were down by 20-some points.
I threw for close to 300 yards
in one quarter, and we came back
and won in the last part of the
game.
And that's how I'm approaching
this game.
I'm going to pull out everything
I can to try to get as far as I
can.
If it gets me there, it gets me
there.
If it doesn't, I'll feel
comfortable the way I played.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How's everybody doing?
>> Pretty good.
>> Good.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge is
for reward, and it will test
your ability with a weapon
called the atlatl.
This is an indigenous Maya
weapon.
It was used to give warriors
more distance when they would
toss a spear in battle.
Today, you're going to use it to
throw an arrow toward a target,
in this case, the center pole.
Each person gets only one throw.
The person who ends up closest
to the target wins this
challenge.
Make sense?
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You are playing for
food.
And the good news is, everybody
here will eat today.
>> Oh, good.
>> PROBST: The bad news is what
you eat will depend on how well
you do in this challenge.
You will leave here and go to a
lodge where you will find nine
meals waiting for you.
First place gets the best meal.
Last place gets the worst meal.
I'll tell you this: first place:
steak and lobster.
(gasping)
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Last place is not.
In addition, the winner of this
challenge gets one clue to the
location of the hidden immunity
idol.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Uh-huh.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for
position, and we'll get started.
All right.
First up, Judd.
>> What do you, say, Judd?
Knock 'em out, buddy.
(applause)
>> PROBST: Judd readies his
toss.
Judd is going to set the mark to
beat.
Good-looking toss.
>> Wow.
>> Nice.
>> Nice throw, Judd.
(applause)
>> That's really nice.
God.
>> PROBST: Judd, just a little
over seven feet.
Judd has set the mark to beat.
Bobby Jon.
>> Come on, Bobby Jon.
>> PROBST: Take a good toss to
beat Judd.
Not going to do it.
Take the second-place spot next
to Judd.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: A little room to play
with.
Judd and Bobby Jon first and
second right now.
Rafe's up.
Feeling confident?
>> Um, I am aiming for medium-
range food today.
(chuckling)
>> PROBST: Nice toss.
>> Nice toss, Rafe.
>> Good job, Rafe.
>> PROBST: Well, Rafe, you're
eating better than Bobby Jon.
That's what we know.
Cindy up next.
Judd in first, Rafe in second,
Bobby Jon in third.
Cindy would like to knock
everybody down one peg.
Nice toss.
>> Oh, nice toss, Cindy.
>> Good job, Cindy.
>> Nice job.
>> PROBST: That's going to be
very close.
Cindy just outside of Judd.
Judd stays in first.
Cindy becomes second, Rafe
third, Bobby Jon fourth.
Lydia.
>> Come on, Lydia.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: Lydia, you got to get
closer than Bobby Jon, or you're
going to end up with the worst
meal.
>> I got the worst meal.
>> PROBST: Take a spot next to
Bobby Jon at the end.
>> Corn soup.
>> PROBST: Danni.
>> Come on, Danni.
>> PROBST: Judd still the mark
to beat.
Danni with a nice toss.
>> Oh, nice throw, Danni.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Danni moves into
third.
>> Good job.
>> Good job, Danni.
>> PROBST: Gary, take your best
shot.
>> Come on, Gary.
>> PROBST: Gary takes a nice
toss.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Very close between
Gary and Rafe.
It's Gary by a few inches.
Gary slides into fourth.
Rafe, Bobby Jon, Lydia move down
a spot.
Stephenie.
Stephenie with a good launch.
>> Good job, Steph.
>> PROBST: Might move her ahead
of Gary.
Steph moves into fourth place.
Gary, Rafe, Bobby Jon, Lydia,
take a step down.
>> You definitely beat me.
>> PROBST: Jamie, you're up.
You know the mark to beat.
A lot of food to be had.
Steak and lobster at the top.
Something much less desirable at
the bottom.
Currently, Lydia is eating that.
Jamie doesn't knock Judd out.
>> Way to go, Judd.
>> Good job.
>> Good job, Judd.
>> You deserve it, man.
You deserve it.
>> PROBST: Jamie, you are just
outside of Danni and in front of
Stephenie.
Jamie, take your spot at number
four.
>> If it's all the same to you,
Jeff, since I had such bad
actions yesterday, I'd like to
take the last-place meal and let
all the other people move up.
>> PROBST: You want to swap your
position?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Do it.
>> Thanks, Jamie.
>> Sorry about that yesterday,
guys.
>> Good job.
>> Jamie, you're all right.
>> PROBST: Jamie, this is a way
to make up for yesterday?
>> We're one tribe now.
I'm sorry I didn't see that
sooner.
>> PROBST: Rafe, how does that
gesture sit with you?
>> I think it shows Jamie
learned a lot and it's awesome.
>> PROBST: Jamie, did you talk
to anybody about doing this?
>> No, sir.
>> PROBST: Did you plan on doing
it all along?
>> I felt in my heart if I
didn't do better than some other
people, then I should give it
up, yes.
>> PROBST: Well, the result of
what you gave up we'll find out
soon, but I promise you, you
gave up a lot moving from fourth
to ninth.
We're going to head over to the
lodge.
Nine meals await.
Judd, steak and lobster.
>> Nice, Judd.
>> PROBST: Let's head out.
Follow me.
>> PROBST: Come on in, Judd.
You're right here.
Everybody else fall in.
Big man gets his own table.
And Jamie, on the end, as he
wished.
Pepito and puppies, they live
here.
Good to be king, huh?
>> Oh, man, feels great, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Let's don't waste any
time.
Bring out the meal.
Steak and lobster for Judd.
>> Oh, my God.
(applause)
>> Oh, man.
>> Whoa, look.
>> PROBST: Judd is going to have
a good night.
>> Judd, take your time, buddy.
>> PROBST: All right, Cindy,
let's bring out your food.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Big plate of food,
chicken, veggies.
>> I cannot even believe this.
>> Oh, my God.
It's more than ample.
>> PROBST: Danni, you ready for
yours?
>> Oh, yeah, bring it on.
>> PROBST: Let's bring out the
next meal.
>> Spaghetti?
>> A big pile of it.
>> Danni.
>> It has meat in it.
>> PROBST: Bring out the next
meal.
>> Oh, nice.
Burger and a beer.
Jamie, I believe that was yours.
This is where you would have
been in the line, Jamie.
>> Nothing tastes better than my
self-respect.
>> PROBST: Well put.
Bring out the next meal.
Slice of pizza for Gary.
Bring out Rafe's meal.
Ham and cheese sandwich.
>> I'm happy.
I still got meat.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, I know
you're hungry.
Baked potato.
>> That will work, man.
>> PROBST: Lydia, you
moved up a spot, thanks to
Jamie.
>> I don't feel like I deserve
it, even if it's one cracker.
>> PROBST: Bring out the next
meal.
How appropriate is this?
>> Oh, a fish.
>> Wow.
>> Wow, that's great.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: Is it really great?
>> It's great because I expected
a cracker.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: Bring out the last
meal.
Jamie wanted this.
You moved yourself down to the
bottom to try and make up for
some remarks you made.
You get the least desirable
meal.
Ramon nuts.
>> Yeah, and dirty water, nice.
>> PROBST: Ramon nuts and water
from your lake.
It has been boiled.
>> Thank you.
Appreciate that.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Two spots on either side of you
open for invite.
If you would like to invite one
or two people to sit with you,
here's what they would get:
the open bar, same as you.
They also get dessert menu, same
as you.
>> This is a tough call, man.
But soon as I walked in the
game, just his arms wide open,
definitely Bobby Jon.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, come up.
Have a seat.
Who's going to sit here?
>> Another one, you know, soon
as I got in the game, man, she
just opened up and welcomed me
like you couldn't believe.
Stephenie.
>> PROBST: Stephenie, bring your
food over.
So have a good night.
No sharing over here.
What you do here is up to you.
The bar is open.
Dessert when you're ready for
it.
One last thing, for you and you
only, a clue to the hidden
immunity idol.
>> Thank you.
Thank you very much.
>> PROBST: Well-earned.
Bon appetit, guys.
>> Good night, Jeff.
>> So I move over to the king
table, and Judd orders a round
of drinks for all of us.
And I split my cheeseburger,
gave Bobby Jon half and Judd
split his steak and gave Bobby
Jon half and we all shared the
lobster.
It was like heaven.
It was unbelievable.
>> I was just craving spaghetti
last night, craving everything.
>> It was a total nine-course
dinner.
But I didn't gorge and pig out,
though.
I didn't want to do that because
I kept looking up at Gary, and I
could see the anguish on his
face, like he really had a small
slice of pizza, and he really
wanted to eat.
I tried to be respectful as I
could when I was eating.
>> I'll take a vodka.
What are you drinking?
>> Vodka, cranberry, but I'm
going to get....
>> Two of them.
You know what, when you make the
vodka, double up on it.
Throw a whole load of vodka and
just a little bit of cranberry.
>> Gary, you're killing me over
there, kid.
>> Why, man?
I'm enjoying watching you.
>> No.
>> You're killing me, dude.
I can't even look at you, man.
>> I won't look at you anymore,
Judd.
>> It was two hours of watching
them gorge themselves and get
drunk.
That's just not my idea of fun.
>> You were giving it one of
these.
>> I'm always throwing it up,
all the time.
(chattering, laughing)
>> Yeah!
>> You got it, buddy.
Judd, a little slower, hon.
>> Okay, we're there.
>> Thank you, Gary.
>> Good job, Judd.
>> Love you.
Love you like a fat kid loves
cake, brother.
I finally get to hug my boy
right here.
Yeah.
>> Judd was pretty well drunk.
He was jovial for a while.
Then Bobby Jon thought he was
going to move this stump to the
fire.
>> Well, it was a 30-foot tree.
>> Ready?
>> One, two, three.
>> Wait a minute.
>> You stay here.
Me and you will... whoa.
>> Let's get it in the morning.
>> We're fine.
>> Give me your hand, Judd.
>> I got it.
>> Oh, my gosh, snoring and
throwing up.
>> Who threw up?
>> Judd.
You got sick, didn't you, last
night?
That was you?
>> No, I got up and went over
there in the ruins somewhere.
>> No, you didn't.
You threw up right in the
shelter.
>> He threw up right next to the
wall.
>> It's all a blur to me, man.
>> Did you get it?
>> Yeah.
>> Did you read it?
>> Is it good?
>> With my reward, the steak and
lobster, I also won a note
giving me a clue to where the
idol is around the jungle.
Now, when it comes to keeping a
secret, man, I can't do it.
>> The clue actually says, "This
idol still eludes you.
It seems nowhere to be found.
It's not buried or concealed nor
directly on the ground."
>> It's got to be like in a
tree.
Judd let me read the clue.
I felt really honored that he
would even think to do that.
Basically what it said is it's
not on the ground.
If you find this, you're
definitely in the final four.
>> Say something, man, tree
mail, I got in my pocket, man,
that thing is definitely by far
on the ground, so to speak.
I mean, I can't give away too
many clues because I'm trying
save my own ass, but it is
totally on the ground.
>> Thanks, Judd, because
that's...
>> I've been looking in trees.
>> I went back to camp and I
told everybody, man, it's on the
ground, it's on the ground.
It ain't on the ground.
It's in a damn tree somewhere.
I don't have a problem lying to
the other guys at all.
That's what the game's about,
man.
>> Okay, your turn.
>> I'm with our plan still.
You know what I'm saying?
I want you to promise you won't
kick me over.
I'll promise you.
>> I'm not going to, Jamie.
>> I swear I won't.
I mean that.
So just stay with me.
>> Okay.
>> No, we're fine.
>> Jamie is paranoid all the
time.
He's always saying, "You're not
going to vote against me, are
you?"
I wish I could say that I
thought what he did by taking
the lowest meal was an act out
of the goodness of his heart.
I don't know if it was.
I don't really think it was.
And so, you know, I don't...
I don't trust Jamie.
>> I think we're getting rid of
Bobby Jon.
>> First?
>> Yeah.
>> You've been honest with me
the whole time.
>> Yeah.
>> Just tell me.
>> You can be pissed at me,
whatever.
I don't care.
I do care, but...
Okay?
I mean, I have to.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> I mean if I don't, I'm dead.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> I told Jamie that I would
vote for whoever they're voting
for tonight, just because it
would be stupid for me to get
them any more mad at me than
there already are.
And there's no breaking that
six.
>> He's voting against me.
>> That's interesting.
I don't know why he told me.
That he just said he's being
honest with everybody and he
wanted everybody to know he's
voting against me today.
>> Huh.
>> Jamie swears that Gary said,
if you don't mind, I'm going to
cast a vote for you tonight, and
we were like, "You sure you
understood?" because sometimes
he's a little... and he's like,
"Yeah."
>> Yeah, no.
I'm out.
>> I think something shady is
going on every time somebody's
talking.
The paranoia sets in.
>> Maybe he is losing it a
little bit out here, like for
real.
>> He definitely is.
>> Like in a real way.
>> Uh-huh, totally.
>> I really see Jamie as a huge
liability and a threat to all of
us because he's just not all
there.
He seems like a loose cannon.
I feel like he can ruin our
entire plan.
I hate walking to tree mail.
>> It's a hike.
>> Yeah.
>> "Balance, speed, dexterity,
There's lots of need to worry.
Move too slow, you could lose it
all,
And be first to join the jury."
It didn't say about wrestling or
fight anybody.
>> That's hard for me.
I feel like it could tip over
right now.
Oh, well, I'll do my best.
>> Gary's balancing over there.
>> He sure is.
>> He told me today he's voting
against me.
>> I wouldn't worry too much
about it.
>> I'll vote him out, too.
That's his... trying to vote me
out.
The game is getting paranoid.
Your mind wonders if people are
going to change your vote.
Stephenie and Rafe could change
over to Bobby Jon and Danni's
side and Gary's side and they'd
have the numbers right now.
>> I don't know why he did that.
>> You got nothing to worry
about.
>> I feel pretty vulnerable,
because I never can
figure out exactly what
everybody's thinking.
I know I have the numbers, but
people change real quick.
This jungle, man, people start
thinking and start thinking too
much.
And then it can all come back
around on you.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
First things first.
Gary.
Immunity back up for grabs.
Today's challenge will test your
coordination and your balance.
On my go, all nine of you will
make your way across a balance
beam, untying two wooden planks
as you go.
Only the first four tribe
members to cross the finish line
with their two planks move on to
the next round.
For the next round, you will use
those two wooden planks to help
you move across a knotted rope
bridge.
The first two to reach the
platform moves on to the final
round.
For the final round, you must
navigate a two-line balance
bridge.
You fall in the water, you go
back to the start.
First person to reach the finish
platform wins immunity.
Make sense?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: We'll get started.
For immunity, first four to
finish move on to the next
round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Got to cross the balance beam
and untie two wooden planks.
Got to untie every knot.
See what you have learned after
24 days.
Jamie going to sit down.
Doesn't want to risk it.
Remaining calm.
Big part of this.
Stephenie working through those
knots quickly.
Gary has his first plank.
He's moving on.
He almost loses it, but keeps
his balance.
Steph goes over and she's got to
go back to the start.
Rafe has his first plank undone.
Jamie has his first plank,
scooching across that balance
beam.
That's going to feel good.
Danni has her first plank.
Cindy, Bobby Jon both have their
first planks.
Judd and Lydia both now have
their first planks.
Everybody working on their
second plank.
Bobby Jon falls off.
He's got to go back to the
start.
Judd, got to go back to the
start, man, your foot.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Gary almost has his
second plank untied.
Steph has her second plank
untied.
She can keep her balance.
She's moving on.
Stephenie moving on to the next
round.
Three more people are moving on.
Gary trying keep his balance,
and he does.
Gary moving on.
Two more moving on.
Jamie's going to be one of them.
And here's Rafe.
That's the four moving on.
Moving on to the next round.
Here we go, guys.
Jamie, Steph, Rafe, Gary, going
to use your planks to move
across this rope bridge.
Two people moving on in this
round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Got to balance your weight with
each step.
Low center of gravity going to
be key.
Gary falls off.
He's back to the start.
Rafe doing very well.
Jamie hanging on.
Steph hanging on.
Gary trying to get back in this.
Immunity at stake.
Still a long way left to go.
Time can be made up.
Steph and Rafe in the lead.
Jamie pulls ahead of Steph.
Gary trying catch up.
Rafe, a good system.
Jamie hanging on.
Rafe getting closer and closer.
Two people moving on.
Gary falls off.
He's out of it.
Rafe very close.
Rafe moving on.
>> Good job, guys.
(Stephenie grunts)
>> PROBST: Jamie moving on.
Rafe and Jamie in the final for
immunity.
Last leg.
Two-line balance bridge.
First one to cross the finish
wins immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First person to get two feet on
the finish platform wins
immunity.
Jamie's got a great system
going.
>> Good job, Jamie.
>> Rafe, hang in there.
>> PROBST: Rafe struggling...
but hangs on.
>> Take your time, Rafe.
>> PROBST: Jamie moving quickly.
>> Good job, Jamie.
>> PROBST: Rafe dangling, dips
in.
Rafe's out.
Rafe in the water.
Got to go back to the start.
Jamie very close to winning
this.
Just like that.
Jamie wins immunity.
>> Good job, Jamie.
Good job, Rafe.
>> PROBST: Well-earned.
>> Good job, Jamie.
>> PROBST: Nice job.
Jamie safe at the vote tonight.
Everybody else fair game.
Tribal Council, see you there.
Head on back to camp.
>> Hmm?
>> I don't like to lose.
I'm so competitive.
>> I hated today.
>> Yeah, he told me that he was
going to vote for me. Yep.
The reason he needs to go is
because he's so headstrong.
>> Yeah.
Cool, I'm sticking to the
plan.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Okay?
>> Perfect.
If anything changes, let us
know.
>> Today, Jamie won immunity,
and, um, I was actually getting
really frustrated with him.
You know, I was thinking maybe
we could get rid of him and be
okay, but he won immunity, so
it's definitely out.
But we've got a great plan in
place, and we're going to get
rid of Gary first.
>> He needs to go because
he's head-gaming everybody.
>> Good.
So are you in with that?
>> Now we have it.
It's the perfect thing.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Why does this seem too easy,
though?
I'm getting nervous, like
something bad's going to happen.
Gary, he's a huge physical
threat in these challenges.
Not to mention he's just always
like in game mode.
So, you know, unfortunately he
just needs to go.
>> Hey, I can guarantee you one
thing, okay?
It's one of us three.
One of us three is going to be
eating good tonight.
>> I've got a 33% chance of
being voted out tonight.
I don't like going to Tribal
Council just because someone's
leaving.
I really don't want to go
tonight because it could be me.
>> Can I just talk to you for a
second?
>> Yeah.
Right here or you want to walk
away?
>> Can I still trust you?
>> Yeah.
>> Look me in the eyes?
>> Are you going to tell me when
I'm going to go?
>> Yeah. If I know I will.
If I know, I'll definitely...
all I know, the plan is... you
know, Bobby Jon, our plan was
you last anyway.
>> Okay.
Well, just keep me informed.
All right?
>> Yeah.
>> Thanks.
It is a game.
When people talk to you, you
don't know if they're lying or
telling the truth.
They're telling me that it's not
me.
They could all be lying to me, I
don't know, so that tells me
that I need that idol.
I've got go find that idol right
now.
>> I want to talk to both of
you.
>> I know I'm out.
>> I know that.
>> That's all I was going to
say.
>> Okay.
Cool.
>> We need you, bud.
>> I went and talked to Judd and
Jamie.
I told them I played with
Stephenie before, great player,
pretty, charming, athletic.
She'll do what she's got to do.
She'll lie to your face and give
you that million-dollar grin.
And she's going to get you guys,
I'm telling you.
They both looked at me and said,
"You're not the one going home
tonight."
I said, "All right."
>> I think it's pretty amazing
that Judd told everybody the
clue that it's on the ground,
and I followed him back here and
he's looking in the trees.
That's pretty interesting.
If it's on the ground, I wonder
why he's looking in the trees.
There's no doubt in my mind that
Judd is lying.
I won't be looking on the
ground.
>> Where did Gary go?
To search for the idol.
>> He went to find the idol.
It would be amazing if he found
it, amazing.
Could you imagine?
>> PROBST: So, Danni, this point
in the game, how big a factor
now does trust become?
>> At this point, it gets kind
of scary who you can trust and
who you can't.
And I'm worried because of the
number game.
And I don't think obviously I
can trust anybody at this point.
My head is on the chopping
block.
I hate that, but it's just part
of the game.
>> PROBST: Rafe, do you agree
with that?
>> Yeah, I think, you know,
there's definitely a lot of
paranoia around camp at this
point in the game.
You see two people go off and
talk, and you're like, "What are
they talking about?
Are they talking about me?
Are they going to vote me off?"
I think that's kind of running
through everyone's head.
But at the same time, you have
to kind of keep your focus and
not let that drive you insane,
because it can in this game.
>> PROBST: Gary, can you lie in
the game of Survivor and not be
breaking any kind of moral code?
>> Well, I think each individual
looks at it differently, and
there's no rule that says you
can't lie in this game.
It's just each individual
looking at what they want to do
and what they want to accomplish
with this game.
>> PROBST: Have you told any
lies?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Judd, you lied in
this game?
>> No, sir, not yet.
You know, it might happen, but
as of this point in the game,
no, I haven't lied about
anything yet.
>> PROBST: Cindy, you trust
these people?
>> Actually, I trust these
people more than I expected.
You spend time with them, you
get to know these people, and
you can't help but develop some
sort of trust in them, but I
don't think it's possible to go
through this game from beginning
to end and never lie to a single
person about anything.
So I think we're all going to be
liars before it's all over with.
>> PROBST: All right, before we
get to the vote, a couple things
to take care of.
Jamie, you have the immunity
necklace.
If you wanted to give it up, you
certainly can.
>> I'm going to hang on to it.
>> PROBST: Okay, the other order
of business, if anybody has
found the immunity idol and
wants to use it tonight, now is
the time to bring it up.
>> Oh, my God!
Gary.
>> Man, good job, Gary.
>> Damn.
>> I knew it.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: All right, no
talking.
Cannot vote for Jamie.
You cannot vote for Gary.
It is time to vote.
Judd, you're up.
>> Wow.
I'm sorry.
>> You just started to take
control of the game, and I don't
know how long it's going to
last, but better now than never,
I guess.
>> I'm glad that you made the
jury if you're the one that goes
tonight, but I could be wrong.
If it's not you, congrats.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Steph.
Steph.
Two votes Steph.
Cindy.
Two votes Steph, one vote Cindy.
Bobby Jon.
Two votes Steph.
One vote Cindy.
One vote Bobby Jon.
Bobby Jon.
That's two for Steph,
two for Bobby Jon.
Bobby Jon.
That's three votes Bobby Jon.
Four votes Bobby Jon.
The tenth person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala,
first member of our jury:
Bobby Jon.
Bring me your torch.
Bobby Jon, the tribe has spoken.
>> Thank you very much.
I enjoyed it.
>> PROBST: See you.
>> Hang in there.
Good luck.
>> PROBST: Well, it's clear from
tonight's Tribal Council that
the next phase of this game is
going to center around lying.
The only problem is, you're
lying to your jury.
Should make for a fun finish.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Jamie gets irritated with Gary.
>> You are calling me a liar.
I don't like it.
>> I did not just call you a
liar.
>> PROBST: The Survivors get
down and dirty for the best
reward yet.
>> Oh, my God.
>> And Lydia is put on the spot.
>> I don't know what to say.
You know?
I mean, it's a hard decision.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> I was very surprised about
the outcome tonight.
I had no clue that Gary was
going to pull out an immunity
idol, and he did.
I mean, I wanted to win the
game, but everything happens for
a reason.
The good Lord didn't want me to
win.
I learned a lot about myself and
communicating with people this
time. I got a chance to do
something that's just a
remarkable and amazing