>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor:
Margaret felt betrayed by Judd.
>> It was me who went the
opposite of what my tribe went.
I'm feeling good about it.
>> Judd flipped the very first
day the new tribe came to be,
and he didn't bother to look
back.
He is a traitor.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready, go!
At the reward challenge, Jamie
was left in the dust, giving
Yaxha a huge win.
>> (whooping)
>> PROBST: Yaxha wins reward.
>> Damn it.
>> PROBST: Back at camp, Yaxha
enjoyed the spoils of victory,
a floating croc-proof swimming
pool.
>> Oh, man, look at this!
>> The reward was spectacular.
I didn't imagine it was going to
be that good.
>> Yaxha! Whoo!
>> PROBST: At Nakum, Stephenie
was frustrated.
>> I mean, I'm sick of losing.
I just feel like I'm in a really
bad dream and I can't get out.
>> PROBST: Over at Yaxha, Blake
was getting on everyone's
nerves.
>> My girlfriend's got big
boobs.
>> Blake is such an idiot.
I have a new favorite game out
here.
It's called "Bait Blake."
>> Blake, what is your absolute
best drunk story?
>> He is digging himself into a
hole and I'm going to do
everything I can to make sure
that he has a shovel.
>> PROBST: In the battle for
immunity, Nakum ended their
losing streak.
For the win, if Nakum gets it...
Nakum wins immunity!
>> Who's smiling now?
>> PROBST: With Tribal Council
looming, Gary, Brian and Amy
were outnumbered.
>> The Yaxha tribe is going
into the Tribal Council
tonight with four old Nakum
members and three old Yaxha
members, so the math is right
there.
>> PROBST: So, they approach the
former Nakum members to turn on
Blake.
>> I hate being the swing vote.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
both Danni and Bobby Jon shook
things up when they turned on
Blake and helped vote him out.
>> PROBST: Blake, the tribe has
spoken.
13 are left, who will be voted
out tonight?
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> The Blake vote opened my eyes
quite a bit because we were four
strong.
Then Blake got voted out.
I'm like, how the heck did that
happen?
You know, people will flip
things around on you.
And you'll find yourself voted
off.
You won't even know how the heck
it happened.
>> What do you think, man?
Any regrets about last night?
>> Um, yeah, some, but that's
just... it was just a part...
a part of that... that was a
stage in the game where I had to
do what I had to do, you know?
I know I liked him.
I know you liked him.
But he was rubbing a lot of
other people the wrong way,
you know?
>> Yeah.
>> Voting off Blake was kind of
like a "get out of jail free"
card for me, Gary and Amy,
because, right now, the numbers
are even.
And so, the bottom line is that
we need to start knocking out
former Nakum members one by one.
It's got to happen.
>> What I don't see is why they
have to bite you through the
shirt.
I mean, do they just have to?
>> This morning is kind of like
every morning.
The mosquitoes are horrible.
Every time it rains, they just
get worse and worse.
>> Mosquitoes are thick.
Like a hundred times worse than
I have ever seen in Florida in
the mangroves in the middle of
the night.
That's how bad it is.
>> Everyone is trying to get
along really hard.
Like, you know, I keep trying to
be positive and it's harder to
do that when someone is being
really a negative energy around
camp, which is what Margaret's
being right now.
After Brooke got voted off, she
was just devastated, and just
took it to so hard.
The six of us get along really,
really well and Margaret is
just, like, kind of fading out.
>> She is miserable, probably
because she got stuck with me
instead of getting stuck with
Brandon.
Instead of getting stuck with
Blake, instead of getting stuck
with Danni or one of them.
She got me.
>> I used to be much higher on
the food chain than I am now.
Now I'm absolutely on the
opposite end after the mix-up.
I'm sure Judd's waiting to get
me off.
I'm not giving up.
But I'm not going to beat my
head against the wall.
I will wait for there to be an
opening.
>> You have somebody that has a
sore thumb walking around camp,
man, miserable.
That puts the team down, man.
We don't need that right now.
>> She just can't grasp the fact
that the old tribe ain't coming
back, man, and this is what
you're stuck with.
>> PROBST: Come on in, Nakum.
Come on in, Yaxha!
Nakum, getting your first look
at the new Yaxha.
Blake voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
You guys ready to get to it?
First things first.
Glad to see that you brought
the immunity idol with you,
as instructed.
It doesn't play a part today,
though.
I will explain that in a minute.
Let's get to today's challenge.
Each tribe will put two people
on opposite sides of a giant
ball.
On my go, both teams will push
the ball against each other.
The object is to maneuver the
ball over your own goal line.
First, you'll put up two women,
then you'll put up two men, then
one of each.
First tribe to score three goals
wins reward.
Want to know what are you're
playing for?
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: It's pretty decent.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Got a barbecue grill,
seven hamburgers, seven hot
dogs, buns, condiments, cold
beer and cold root beer.
So the good news is the winning
tribe will feast today.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: The bad news is
tonight, both tribes are going
to Tribal Council.
Both tribes are voting somebody
out.
Two people are going home.
There is another element to
this.
In addition to the barbecue
feast, the winning tribe earns
the right to compete in another
challenge immediately following
this one for individual
immunity.
One tribe member will win this
immunity necklace.
One tribe member will be safe at
their Tribal Council tonight.
That person will also sit in on
the other tribe's Tribal Council
where they will be able to
gather information.
And in a game where knowledge is
power, this is a crucial
opportunity.
Nakum, you have one extra
member.
You're sitting somebody out.
>> Lydia.
>> PROBST: Lydia, take a seat on
the bench.
We will randomly draw for each
round.
Steph and Cindy taking on Amy
and Danni.
Survivors ready?
Go!
The race for the ball.
Cindy and Steph there first, get
a bit of a lead.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Danni makes a big
surge.
>> Push!
>> Go, Amy!
>> PROBST: Danni and Amy getting
squeezed.
Danni squeezing that tree.
>> Come right, Amy.
Push right!
>> PROBST: Danni has to work
around the tree.
Cindy and Steph still with a bit
of an advantage.
>> Coming your way, Amy!
>> To the right!
Amy, get on the other side of
the ball!
The other side of the ball!
>> PROBST: Amy and Danni getting
some movement on that ball.
>> Push!
>> Go around.
Go around!
>> PROBST: Amy and Danni with
another surge.
Cindy and Steph on their heels,
Amy and Danni got a lot of
momentum now.
Cindy and Steph fighting to keep
them off.
>> Other side!
>> This way, Steph.
>> PROBST: Amy pushing, she
wants that barbecue.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: That's it.
Yaxha scores!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: One-zero.
Next round, it's the men:
Brandon and Bobby Jon taking on
Judd and Jamie.
Yaxha leads one-zip,
playing to three.
Survivors ready, go!
It's a race to the ball.
Both guys bang into the ball!
>> Push it out! Push it out!
>> Push it out, let's go.
>> PROBST: Judd and Jamie making
a surge.
Judd and Jamie picking up
ground!
>> Good work, guys.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon and Brandon
pushing back now.
Bobby Jon and Brandon making up
a little ground.
More ground.
Bobby Jon with a big push.
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Yaxha making up a lot
of ground all of a sudden.
Amy and Judd go left.
>> Yes, Judd, yes!
>> PROBST: Brandon on his feet,
on his knees.
Brandon down again.
Jamie and Judd working hard,
making up a lot of ground.
Jamie and Judd, down to 10 feet,
down to five feet!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Nakum scores!
(yelling)
>> PROBST: Next round, one man,
one woman from each tribe.
Judd and Steph taking on Gary
and Amy, we are tied 1-1 playing
to three.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's a race to the ball.
>> Good job! Good job!
>> PROBST: Judd and Steph get
the early advantage.
Gary and Amy now wedging Steph
against the tree.
>> Push it this way!
>> PROBST: Steph and Judd make
the quick maneuver, make up some
ground.
Amy's down!
Go!
>> PROBST: Amy's hurt!
Big advantage for Steph and
Judd!
And they're taking advantage of
it, pushing it further and
further back.
Gary and Amy giving it up.
Nakum scores!
Nakum leads 2-1.
Amy is hurt.
Amy, next round is women again.
>> I should do it.
>> PROBST: Are you ready to go?
>> Not really, but I'm going to
do it.
>> PROBST: All right, good.
Next two women take a spot.
Here's where we stand:
Nakum leads 2-1.
We're playing to 3.
It's women on women.
Yaxha only has two women, Amy's
got to go again, even with a
hurt ankle.
For a reward and a shot at
individual immunity--
Survivors, ready, go!
>> Come on! Come on!
>> PROBST: Margaret and Cindy
with a big advantage right now.
Danni and an injured Amy trying
to fight them off.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: And they're doing it
right away with an advantage.
Danni and Amy pushing Margaret
and Cindy back.
Margaret and Cindy pushing back
now.
Margaret and Cindy, now trying
to hold off Danni and an
injured Amy.
>> Push!
>> Get on the left!
>> PROBST: Cindy wedged up
against the tree, they lost
a lot of ground.
Amy and Danni with huge
momentum.
Yaxha scores.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: We are tied 2-2!
>> Yes!
Yes!
>> PROBST: We are tied up 2-2,
this point will decide it,
barbecue feast, shot at
individual immunity at stake.
We have a new matchup for
Yaxha.
Bobby Jon and Brian taking on
Judd and Jamie for Nakum.
Survivors, ready, go!
>> Go, go!
Yeah!
>> Your ball, your ball!
Yes!
>> PROBST: Brian shoved against
the tree.
He's lost a lot of leverage.
(shouting)
Judd is down!
Bobby Jon and Brian pushing,
making up ground into the
obstacle.
>> Go! Go! Go!
>> PROBST: Jamie and Judd get
some momentum going.
Bobby Jon and Brian trying to
hold them off.
Judd and Jamie getting closer
for Nakum.
And they have it!
Nakum wins a barbecue feast and
a shot at individual immunity.
>> PROBST: Yaxha, good effort.
Amy coming back strong,
not enough.
No reward, no shot at individual
immunity.
The only thing you have to look
forward to is Tribal Council
tonight.
I will see you there.
Head on back to camp.
Nakum, good effort.
Two victories in a row.
Barbecue feast is yours.
But that is later.
We're not through here yet.
One more challenge.
Somebody is going to get
individual immunity for
tonight's Tribal Council.
Follow me and I will explain.
All right, the barbecue feast is
already yours.
But this is what you should be
concentrating on now.
One of you gets a shot at
individual immunity.
Here's how it works:
On my go, all seven of you will
race out into the field to
collect three bags of letter
tiles.
Each time you untie a bag, you
got to bring it back to your
station.
Once you've collected all three
bags, untie them, empty out 11
letters.
Use those 11 letters to form a
two-word phrase.
First person to spell that
phrase correctly wins immunity,
safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Clear?
Take a spot.
We'll get started.
For immunity, Survivors ready?
Go!
Each time you untie a bag, you
bring it back to your station.
Once you have all three bags,
you untie the bags, empty out
the letters, start spelling the
word.
Steph back with her first bag,
Cindy back with her first bag.
Margaret back with her first
bag.
Lydia, Rafe, Jamie, back with
his bag.
Judd bringing up the rear with
his first bag.
Stephanie back with bag number
two.
Cindy back with bag number two.
Margaret and Rafe with their
second bags.
Lydia with her second bag.
Jamie with bag number two.
Stephanie has her third bag, she
can begin emptying the tiles.
Cindy back with her third bag.
Rafe in it now.
Margaret and Jamie in it now.
Judd in it now.
Two-word phrase-- when you think
you have it, yell it out.
Steph has all of her letter
tiles out.
Margaret has all her tiles out.
>> I can't get it freakin' out
of the bag, man.
>> PROBST: Judd having trouble
even getting his tiles out.
Margaret trying to figure it
out.
Rafe very close.
Ancient ruin... ancient ruin...
ancient ruin.
>> PROBST: Two word phrase, when
you think you have it, yell it
out.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Stop!
Rafe has it first.
Ancient Ruin.
Rafe wins immunity.
>> Rafe?
>> Thanks.
>> Thank you.
>> Judd had it, but he didn't
have the puzzle.
Damn! I had it!
Next time I got to keep my
mouth shut, man.
>> PROBST: So Judd, you weren't
in this challenge at all, you
figure out the phrase and say it
and Rafe gets it.
>> I didn't know I was that
smart, man.
>> PROBST: Rafe is wearing
immunity.
Rafe, come on over.
>> Great stuff!
>> PROBST: Turn around.
You are safe tonight at Tribal
Council.
So, you guys have a barbecue
feast.
Grab it and head out.
>> (whoops)
>> Oh, my God!
>> Way to go, Nakum!
>> Good job!
>> Whoo! We did it again, kids.
>> We're on a winning streak.
>> Today was an amazing day.
Today we won the barbecue and
then we had individual immunity
and I won the first individual
immunity, which is awesome!
>> Good job!
>> Right here, baby.
Whoo!
That was just an all-around
good day, man.
>> No kidding.
>> What happened to Bobby Jon,
man?
>> Today in that reward
challenge, man, Bobby Jon hit a
flip switch, man.
I was just waiting for him to
swing, 'cause I was just going
to block that and knock him
right there.
>> He always does that.
>> Why? I'm like why?
>> Is he crazy?
>> The guy got right in my face
and started screaming because I
was happy because we won.
So I started screaming back.
I thought it was about to go to
blows, you know.
Just Southern people, we're
crazy and we know it.
>> Here's to Nakum.
>> To Nakum.
>> And our families that can't
be with us.
>> Thank you, guys.
>> Thank you, God.
>> Who the hell wants to go to
Tribal Council?
It sucks.
You know?
Two in a row, one night after
the other.
It's horrible.
>> Keep going.
You too, Danni.
>> Well, we all gave everything,
I mean, you know.
That's just, they're just
bigger, more weight, that's all.
>> We just can't dwell on it.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Whoa. Whoa!
>> Jamie is kind of cocky and
arrogant and there is a line
crossed with me.
And he crossed it today.
And I just went over there and I
put him in his place.
>> You know, there's another
bear out in the woods, too.
>> I am concerned.
I felt I let them down when I
fell that second time I went out
there.
I went to go push back and my
same ankle goes and it snaps.
I wasn't sure what actually
happened.
But, you know, it's okay, 'cause
I went out there the next time.
It's swollen, but I can live
with it.
>> As a tribe, we're three
former Yaxha, and three former
Nakum, everybody is vulnerable.
You know, it might be an easy
vote to vote out Amy tonight,
but would it be our smartest
vote down the road because Gary
and I will be outnumbered by
three former Nakum.
>> Brian wants to rejoin Yaxha
to stay strong, but the weak
part of his plan is, why would I
get rid of Bobby Jon, one of the
strongest players on this team?
>> We will win the next one,
I guess.
>> Amy and Brian are probably in
the biggest threat of getting
voted off.
Because I don't know what kind
of alliances they have.
But you know, they're probably
the physically weaker players.
>> Of the six of us, any one
could go home tonight.
There's no one who is safe.
Nobody has immunity and we're
all looking to get each other
out of this game so we can get
further.
And I'm just hoping that Gary
and Amy aren't pulling the wool
over my eyes and everybody just
ends up voting for me.
Because honestly, anything,
anything can happen at Tribal
Council tonight.
>> Oh, my God!
>> I never had a hamburger taste
like this.
>> It doesn't get better than
this.
>> The only thing that sucks
about this, man, is that we've
got to go to freakin' Tribal
Council.
I just hate that.
>> Just gearing up for that,
it sucks, man.
>> Even though we won the
reward, the barbecue, and I won
individual immunity, both tribes
still have to go to Tribal
Council.
So it kind of takes a little
something out of the victory
because nobody ever wants to go
to Tribal Council.
>> So we're down to what, we
lose Margaret tonight,
then we're down to how many,
what, six, right?
>> Yeah, six.
>> I think Margaret knows she's
going.
She's not even trying to put up
a fight.
>> She's always on the
sidelines, man.
>> I go to Tribal Council
tonight, man, not a damn worry
in the world, man.
Hell, no, man, they need me,
man.
I'm one of the big guns here,
I'm not saying I'm going
overboard, but I feel, you know,
I can do what I want around
these people.
Rafe, you sure you don't want
that beer?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man, I got no problem
taking it.
>> Judd is the person, I think,
as a tribe member and
as a person, is the most
offensive to the tribe.
>> (belches)
>> I give you the whole beer,
you give me your hot dog.
>> You want to switch?
>> Absolutely.
So now I got two beers.
>> Well, no, there's only two
left.
>> Judd does what Judd wants to,
when he wants to and how he
wants to.
The funny part is Judd's
Judd's biggest enemy.
>> There's only two beers left.
>> Uh-oh.
>> I definitely got one coming,
without a doubt.
>> No, one beer's mine.
These are mine.
Each were supposed to have
two beers and one root beer.
But, somehow, it ended up that
what's left does not equal out
to what is owed.
So basically, we have a
beer-root beer conundrum.
>> Who's hiding the beer, man?
>> There's three beers left.
What are you talking about?
>> One is Cindy's half-full one.
>> Whenever Judd screws up, Judd
makes a big deal about it,
and tries to make it a whole
explosion so it kind of diffuses
the focus on him.
>> I don't understand this whole
beer thing.
How are we not...?
>> I don't either.
>> It doesn't make any sense.
>> I know.
>> We will never figure it out.
>> Yeah, but who?
Whoever drank the beer is
going home tonight.
>> Judd's got to watch his
mouth.
He gets so pumped up.
And his mouth works before his
brain does.
>> You had two from you.
And you had one of his and whose
else's?
>> How many beers do I have
left?
I had two, right?
>> I felt like I freaking
deserved it anyway, if I took an
extra beer, you wouldn't be
eating damn hot dog and this
cheeseburger if it wasn't for
me.
>> You know what, everybody can
kiss my ass.
And I hope you enjoyed your hot
dog and your hamburger today.
>> He's got to stop and think
about what he's saying before it
comes out of his mouth.
Because outbursts of
inconsideration like that is
going to be a negative mark on
his slate.
And in the end, that could come
back to get him.
>> PROBST: All right.
Let's start with the
fun stuff first.
Steph, tell me about the feast.
>> It was awesome.
We cooked the hamburgers up
right away.
There were a coup of trades
going on, beer for root beer,
root beer for beer.
I traded Judd for a hot dog.
He took my beer.
>> Judd, you gave up food for
beer?
>> Oh, yeah, man.
Without a doubt, I'll give up a
hot dog for a beer, any day,
Jeff.
Out here in 122 degree weather,
I will take a beer any day,
buddy.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's challenge.
Jamie, what happened between you
and Bobby Jon?
>> I celebrated when I won,
because I had so much energy.
And he hates losing, so he was
in my face yelling.
I'm from the South; only thing
I know how to do is yell back.
>> PROBST: Margaret, does this
tribe have good sportsmanship?
Are you guys good sports?
>> That's tough, Jeff,
because Judd is very vocal and
Jamie can be very expressive.
And they don't hesitate to just
blurt it all out there.
Sometimes you have to learn to
control your emotions when you
are on the ball field.
>> PROBST: Judd, chomping at the
bit-- what's on your mind?
>> I don't know what the heck
Margaret is talking about.
I mean, it's not like we're
being bad sportsmanships at all.
We just go out there and we give
it 120 damn percent, man.
Whatever it takes, we'll give
it.
That's what I did today, and
everybody ate good.
So, no matter what I do, I'm
giving it my damn all, man.
>> PROBST: Giving it your damn
all doesn't mean you are a good
sport or bad sport.
There is no equal sign between
those two words.
>> A win is a win, man.
If we did good, we are going to
go out there and go crazy, man.
It's like scoring a damn
touchdown in a football game.
That gives us more motivation to
keep going and going, man.
Drive it right to them, man.
Keep driving it to them.
That is what we are doing.
I mean, that's not bad
sportsmanship.
We just keep on driving and
driving, man.
We'll drive that ball all the
way down field until we score a
touchdown, man.
>> Judd.
>> You know what?
You probably never played a damn
sport in your life, anyway,
so you don't even know what it
is like, man, so you should just
shut up.
>> This is what happens all the
time.
When Judd gets vocal, Judd plows
over anybody in front of him.
He trash talks anybody he
doesn't like.
And that's not good
sportsmanship.
I'm not saying the whole tribe
is unsportsman but I have seen
it, especially from Judd.
>> PROBST: Judd, you look like
if I would let you, you would go
over and strangle Margaret right
now.
>> I'm just... you know, playing
sports my whole life, man,
I wouldn't consider myself a bad
sportsmanship.
>> Uh-huh.
>> This team that I have here,
man, is awesome.
I love it, man.
Except for Margaret, I love this
damn team, man.
>> PROBST: Cindy, does this
hostility between Judd and
Margaret concern you a little
bit?
>> Well, it concerns all of us
because we all have to live, you
know, in the same group together
and deal with it.
And when we have two people that
don't like each other very much,
it puts a little bit of
negativity into the air.
And negativity is not good for
the entire tribe.
>> PROBST: Margaret?
>> Judd doesn't listen to
anybody.
Judd only listens to Judd.
>> Let's ask the other team if
Judd listens to anybody.
Cindy, do I listen to everybody?
>> Yeah...
>> Okay, Rafe, do I listen to
everybody?
>> I... I honestly think that...
>> Rafe, have an opinion.
Just say yes or no.
>> I'm saying my opinion right
now.
Time-out.
>> Stephanie when you talk to
me, do I listen to you?
>> Yes, yes.
>> Do I listen to you?
Do I listen to you?
>> Yes.
>> There you go.
>> But this is what Judd does,
Judd bullies, and that's just
what he does.
>> You're full of it, man.
Get out of here.
>> PROBST: Rafe, put you on the
spot a little bit.
Are you intimidated a little bit
by Judd?
>> I'm really not.
I totally was really nervous
about being on the tribe with
Judd.
Judd has a temper, it's obvious,
but he has been good to me since
the day I walked on to this
tribe.
>> I just think Judd's high
strung.
He's a lot like me-- can't sit
still.
It's hard for him to keep....
>> When I first walked into
camp, she's telling me that I
have A.D.D.
That's how you approach me.
That is what you like to say.
She comes to camp:
"You have A.D.D.
Do you know that?"
When you first meet somebody, is
that something nice to say?
Is that a compliment?
I have A.D.D.?
>> The other problem with Judd
is he has a problem with recall.
>> Yeah.
Did you or did you not, soon as
you saw me, did you tell me that
I had A.D.D.?
Is that true or is that false?
Don't ask me such a stupid
question, man.
>> This is what it is like to
try to talk to him.
>> Yeah, because I don't want to
talk to you.
And don't talk to me.
I won't talk to you, man, that's
it.
>> PROBST: So, Judd, not a big
question who are you voting for.
>> Not a big question at all,
man.
>> PROBST: I have really never
ever seen anything like this,
and I will be honest with you, I
have never seen such...
>> Hey, Jeff, can I say
something first?
>> PROBST: Of course.
>> Let me say something.
She was so miserable that the
other tribe wasn't coming back,
and she got stuck with me.
That's the bottom line, man.
I'm telling you, that's what
happened.
>> What happened, Jeff, is
within two hours, he was up that
pyramid, already flipping over
on us.
It was four old Nakum,
four old Yaxha.
We had a chance to stay strong.
He rolled over right away.
>> You would you have done the
same damn thing to me too, man,
if you had the opportunity.
>> I didn't. I didn't.
>> Trust me.
>> PROBST: Steph, how do you
trust somebody who so quickly
dismisses their old tribe and
says, "No, you are my new
friends now."
>> Because that is his old
tribe.
We are the new tribe.
I think he embraced his new
tribe and is willing to go as
far as we can go together with
this tribe.
What's he going to be like, "Oh,
I'm not going to talk to you
guys, because my old tribe is
not on my tribe anymore"?
It's retarded.
>> PROBST: You know, tonight,
watching what is going on with
this group, there is a lot of
hostility.
Cindy, do you think it ends with
tonight's Tribal Council?
Do you get rid of the bad apple
and now the tribe is sound and
complete?
>> I think it will be okay for
awhile.
We'll have to see what happens
in the future.
But I think we all know what we
have to do.
>> PROBST: Well, let's find out
what it is you have to do.
Rafe is the only person you
cannot vote for.
It is time to vote.
Jamie, you're up.
>> Hey, Margaret, if you leave
this jungle now, it ain't soon
enough, man.
Get out, now.
>> Judd, you are a bully.
You are self-righteous, you're
rude, you're profane-- no one
like you deserves a million
dollars.
My vote is for you, buddy.
>> PROBST: I will go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Margaret.
Judd.
One vote Margaret, one vote
Margaret: two votes Margaret.
Margaret: three votes Margaret.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala.
Margaret, that's four, that's
enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Margaret, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, to paraphrase your words,
tonight you got rid of the
problem.
If that's true, it should mean
happy days at Nakum.
As part of winning individual
immunity today, Rafe earned the
right to listen in on Yaxha's
Tribal Council.
Rafe, you will move over to the
jury area.
Everybody else, grab your
torches.
Head on back to camp.
>> This is probably
physically the most challenging
thing that I've ever had to do
in my life.
And I'm so excited that I did
it.
Best wishes to Nakum tribe.
I'm sure that a lot of tension
will be gone now.
But I think you will have
a lot of troubles with Judd.
So take care.
>> PROBST: Now bring in Yaxha.
>> PROBST: Rafe is going to be
listening in on your Tribal
Council tonight.
It is a right he earned
along with winning individual
immunity today.
Let's talk about today's
challenge.
Bobby Jon, what happened with
you and Jamie?
>> I just got in the heat of the
moment, you know.
Sometimes when two males are
competing against each other,
it's like two bulls in a ring.
You just get aggressive and you
know it just kind of came out.
Two male people, a lot of
testosterone built up and we
both want to win.
>> PROBST: Gary, do you consider
Nakum to be good sports?
>> I would say, yes.
Every once in a while, I would
say maybe Jamie has a tendency
to get a little excited and
maybe talk some trash our way,
but on the whole, I would say
yes.
>> PROBST: Brian, you come
into this game with a certain
tendency to work up here.
And now are you being tested
with your body.
Do you feel a change happening?
>> I have always been an
athletic person.
So I knew I could take whatever
was handed to me.
So when it's time to bring out
the physical, I will definitely
bring it out.
But when it's time to bring out
the mental, I'll have that ready
too.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, what's
your take on Brian?
>> I mean, if you want to find
a kamikaze that will bust a
wedge, this is the man who about
do it.
>> PROBST: A kamikaze that is
going to bust a wedge.
>> This boy right here, he's
constantly thinking Survivor.
The guy knows his game.
He is just a good old boy, you
know?
He would be a great neighbor.
>> PROBST: Danni, did you ever
think you would say Bobby Jon
say about Brian, "He's just a
good ol' boy"?
>> You know, our first
impression of Brian, when we
were over at Nakum, was he's
strong, and he's just such a
gentleman, too, it is all I can
say about him.
He is definitely strong, he's
smart but he is a classy, classy
guy.
>> PROBST: All right, now let's
talk about Amy's chronic
injury to that ankle.
So Amy, how is the ankle?
>> It's good.
I tweaked it a little bit, but I
tripped and fell too.
>> PROBST: Tweaked it a little
bit?
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: Brandon, had to be a
little impressed because, after
Amy went down, she could barely
get off of that field, only to
turn around and have to go back
out again.
>> Oh, man, Jeff, you have no
idea how impressed I was.
I mean, Amy got that look on her
face and just started going at
it, limping and cussing and
everything.
I was, like, man, you know,
that is what I like to see-- I
mean, go above the odds, you
know, and Amy did.
I'm like...
I was so impressed with her
today.
>> PROBST: So Bobby Jon, there
doesn't appear to be an obvious
weak link.
But you got to get rid of
somebody-- what do you base it
on?
>> Jeff, that's a real good
question.
I think today we all did a lot
of soul-searching and we know
that nobody has done anything
wrong to leave.
Everybody's giving 110% in
a challenge.
Everybody is giving 110% around
camp.
You know, you look up, and
somebody's throwing a corn cake
in your mouth, you know,
it going to be a tough
one but like you said, it's
going to happen and this is the
way it is.
>> PROBST: All right, one more
thing before the vote.
In addition to Rafe being able
to sit in and listen to your
Tribal Council, he also earned
the right to give one of you
immunity.
Okay, Rafe, here's how it will
work:
Write the name of the person you
want to give immunity to, put it
in an envelope, seal it, put it
in the voting urn.
Then come down and get your
torch and head on back to your
camp.
Go make your vote.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: You can leave your
immunity necklace behind.
Good night.
Okay, Yaxha, Rafe's choice for
immunity will remain a secret
until after your vote.
Gary, you're up.
>> This would be the outwit part
of "outwit, outplay, outlast."
>> Brian, you are a great kid
with a ton of heart.
You have done a remarkable job.
You should be proud of yourself.
>> PROBST: I will go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Bobby Jon.
Brian-- one vote Brian,
one vote Bobby Jon.
Brian: two votes Brian.
Brian: that's three votes Brian,
one vote Bobby Jon.
Brian: that's four votes, that's
enough to vote you out.
You have one shot left.
Rafe's immunity.
Brian, Rafe gave immunity to
Gary.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala is Brian.
>> Good jobs guys, good luck.
>> Good luck, Brian.
>> PROBST: Brian, the tribe has
spoken.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Well, I got to hand
it to you.
You did a great job of pumping
Brian up and making him feel
secure.
And then you cut his throat.
If it could happen to him,
it could happen to you.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, Amy confronts Gary.
>> Give me the lowdown
on Mr. Gary Hawkins,
ex-professional football player.
>> Yeah, I wish.
>> If you are and I find out
after, I'm going to beat you
down.
>> PROBST: And Nakum gets an
unexpected visit.
>> Nakum!
>> I think the other tribe is
coming to visit.
here.
>> Hi!
>> Well, I certainly went down
fighting-- I know I played this
game very hard.
I did everything I could and I
did not see that coming, which
is how I wanted to go out.
So the fact they pulled one over
on me, I'm really proud of them.
I'm glad they are playing the
game.
I never really had to push
myself like that before.
So I will take from this
experience the fact that I was
able to go into a really
difficult situation and come out