>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, Lydia was relieved
she had been spared at Tribal
Council.
>> You know, I don't deserve to
go.
I'm a hard worker.
So, you know, I'm happy that I'm
here.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the tribes played for
comfort items.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Yaxha started with a solid lead.
Take off your blindfolds!
Start assembling.
>> Girls on tie, boys build.
>> PROBST: But Nakum made up
time when they discovered how to
correctly assemble their tent.
Nakum wins reward!
(cheering)
Back at camp, the guys struggled
with how best to use their new
tarp.
So Margaret spoke up.
>> If you're going to slant it,
you got to decide which way you
want to slant it.
>> PROBST: And Bobby Jon and
Judd got annoyed.
>> I'm 28 years old.
You just can't tell grown men
what to do all the time.
>> She's playing that mother hen
role.
>> PROBST: At Yaxha, Brian
pumped up his team.
>> We got it, guys! We need it.
We're the underdogs.
Do it for your family, do it for
whatever, do it for each other.
Just do it!
And win, guys!
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, the tribes competed
in an ancient Maya court ball
game.
Temperature update: 114 degrees.
Yaxha struggled when Amy
sprained her ankle and Brianna
and Lydia couldn't pull it
together.
>> Why don't you move it!
I want to see some hustle.
>> PROBST: Nakum won their
second immunity in a row.
Danni scores!
Nakum wins immunity.
Back at Yaxha, Steph was
discouraged.
>> I'm frustrated because we
have Amy, she can't run.
And we have a fish monger.
And we have Brianna, who is a
makeup artist.
Why, just once, can't I just be
on a great tribe?
>> PROBST: With Lydia, Amy and
Brianna all at risk, the tribe
ultimately voted out the one
they considered the weakest.
Brianna, the tribe has spoken.
15 are left.
Who will be voted off tonight?
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(birds chirping)
>> Being here is the hottest
conditions I've ever been in in
my life.
Hotter than I could possibly
imagine.
I mean, we're talking triple
digits every day, and it seems
like every day it goes up a
couple of digits more.
Just when you think like 104,
holy crap, that is the hottest
I could possibly imagine,
the next day it's 114.
>> I tell you, you take the heat
and you get near a fire, it's
even worse.
>> Uh-huh.
>> The tribe's pretty tired.
We're weak after yesterday's
challenge.
It was like nothing we had ever
dreamed of.
Heat absolutely wiped us out.
It's brutal.
And you can't do anything.
You're sapped of energy.
And the mosquitoes are
unbelievable.
>> I've never seen anything like
the bugs in my life.
In my entire...
you know what?
They just, it's like you ever
watch The Killer Bees, the
movie?
They're all over you.
I mean, they're literally, if I
didn't have my sweatshirt on,
forget about it.
>> We were smacking and kind of
fight sparring in the wind, man,
just trying to get the
mosquitoes out of there, but it
ain't gonna work, man.
It only works for about maybe a
millimeter of a second.
Then the thing goes and he's
right back at you.
>> I know, man, we have a bunch
of bites.
>> They're brutal today.
>> Yeah, this, this place
changes you out here.
I mean, between starving and the
heat and mosquitoes and bugs,
everything adds up, and it just,
you know, completely wears you
down.
So I find it's just easier to
lay around and do nothing.
I guess, which is kind of
pathetic, but, I don't know,
we're still on top, you know.
We're beating the other team.
I mean, I can't imagine how the
other team feels if we're not
feeling very well.
I mean, God knows what it's like
around their place.
>> Now, that's the method we
need to start using.
>> Oops.
>> It's going down.
>> Quick, quick, quick.
>> I got him.
>> There we go.
>> How many you have total?
>> Four so far.
>> Whoa!
>> There's the ticket right
there.
>> So the method for today was
sit this big pot down in the
water that had all the cornmeal
in it.
And then all the minnows swarm
inside of it in a big circle.
And then you pull it out
really fast and at least a
couple of them are still in
there.
>> I saw it, I saw it.
There he is.
They hide in the bottom.
>> Basically, we're a finally
tuned fishing machine.
Gary and I, there's no stopping
us.
These minnows are in trouble.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Looks like a croc, if you ask
me.
>> I'd say you're right.
>> I think it probably is.
>> Wow!
>> We were all down
at the dock, and we look out
into the flat lake, and all of a
sudden, we see this huge croc,
and he seemed pretty long.
>> He's coming this way.
>> Oh.
>> Oh, my God!
It's the Loch Ness Monster.
(gasps)
>> Wow!
>> He went and suddenly
he caught a fish and we saw that
big mouth eat it.
We were like, uh-oh, that could
have been one of us if we were
swimming across its path.
>> Ow!
>> What?
>> A fish got me.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Nakum getting your first look at
the new Yaxha tribe.
Brianna voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Take a seat on the bench.
Well, it's day nine and you guys
have endured arguably the
toughest Survivor ever.
So you've earned a little
relief.
Today we're going to give you a
break from the challenges, and
instead give you a chance to
learn a little bit about what
your tribe mates think about
you.
At the same time, you'll gain a
little insight into the other
tribe.
I'm going to ask you a series of
questions about your tribe
mates.
You'll write your answers down,
reveal them to me.
Keep in mind each answer will
have a direct effect on those
tribe mates.
Make sense?
Let's get started.
First question: which tribe
member is most in need of some
nourishment?
You cannot vote for yourself.
I know everybody's hungry, but
which tribe member in particular
most needs some nourishment?
All right, reveal.
Yaxha is almost a slam dunk for
Jamie as most in need of some
nourishment.
For Nakum, everybody voting for
Danni.
Danni, Jamie, come on up.
>> Oh.
(all sigh)
>> PROBST: They're yours.
Dig in.
Take a bite.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> PROBST: It's not a race.
It's yours.
>> Mmm.
>> Go ahead, Jamie.
You deserve it.
>> PROBST: All right.
Next question: which tribe
member is the smelliest?
Who smells the worst on your
tribe?
That's got to be a tough one.
Margaret says, nope, easy.
Let's reveal.
For Yaxha, we have three Jamies
and four Garys.
All right.
Gary gets designated the
smelliest.
And for Nakum, we have four
Bobby Jons.
That's enough.
Bobby Jon and Gary, come
forward.
>> Go get it, Gar.
>> PROBST: What I have for you
two is right over there.
Five gallons of fresh water and
a bush shower.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Nice backbones there, guys.
>> PROBST: Gary not wasting any
water.
>> There's shampoo there, Bobby
Jon.
>> Use all that soap.
>> Don't romance it, sweetheart.
>> Oh, he's scrubbing.
Look at the lather.
>> Oh, man.
>> Use all that soap.
>> PROBST: Margaret, you got
shower envy.
>> Oh, my God, I do.
>> Gary, we're going to
be smelling you all night, just
sniffing.
>> PROBST: I can't say you look
a lot different.
>> Thanks, guys.
Yo, baby-- mmm!
>> PROBST: Next question: from
your tribe, which man and which
woman most deserves a picnic
afternoon atop an ancient Maya
pyramid, returning to their camp
later this afternoon?
Put down one woman and one man.
Reveal.
For Yaxha, it looks like it is
Gary.
The man.
And we have Amy, the woman.
For Nakum, we have Margaret.
For the men, it looks like it is
Judd.
>> Yes, thank you, man.
>> PROBST: All four people, come
on up.
Amy, you look like you're going
to cry.
>> What is it, a tarantula?
>> PROBST: I wouldn't do that to
you.
>> Oh, my God!
(cheering, sobbing)
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
>> PROBST: We have chicken,
potato salad, huge chocolate
chip cookies, and iced tea.
You guys have been rewarded with
a nice picnic.
Eat it all.
You can't bring it back.
There's no burden on you.
>> Guys, man, I love you,
man.
>> PROBST: Next question, of the
people remaining, which tribe
member has the most tribe pride?
Who just bleeds Yaxha blue?
Who bleeds Nakum yellow?
Who has the most tribe pride?
Okay, reveal.
Yaxha, it is three votes Brian,
two votes Steph.
Brian noted as tribe member with
the most tribe pride.
For Nakum, Cindy has four votes.
Cindy noted as having the most
tribe pride.
So, Brian, you have the most
tribe pride for Yaxha.
It's only fitting you remain a
Yaxha member.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Take a spot on the
Yaxha mat.
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: Jamie, Rafe, Lydia
and Steph, drop your buffs.
You are now members of Nakum.
You're switching tribes.
Come on up, get a buff, have a
spot on the Nakum mat.
Cindy, meet your new tribe
members.
>> Hey, Cindy.
>> PROBST: Now Nakum, because
you have one extra member, one
of you will remain a Nakum
member.
The other four will join Brian
on the Yaxha tribe.
There are five buffs here.
One of them is Nakum yellow.
You're going to draw to decide
your fate.
You decide who draws and what
order.
It's up to you.
Danni fields blue.
You're now a member of Yaxha.
Who's next?
Brooke, choose your fate.
You stay with Nakum.
That settles the rest of it.
Bobby Jon, Blake, Brandon,
you're all now members of Yaxha.
Gary and Amy will be returning
to the Yaxha camp later for a
bit of a surprise.
Nakum, Judd and Margaret will be
returning to your tribe, also in
for a bit of a surprise.
Head on back to camp.
Get to know each other.
>> Wow, man!
Top of the world.
>> How about a toast?
Guys, to Guatemala.
>> Yes.
(indistinct chatter)
>> The location of this
picnic was great.
We were above this whole area
here.
We could see everything, the
whole lake.
You could see, I'm going to
guess, 30 miles.
>> Oh, my God!
It's so good.
Oh, wow!
>> Where are you from,
Amy?
>> Boston.
>> Are you?
We were trying to guess your
accent.
It was either New York or
Boston.
>> Boston.
>> That's what we were figuring
out.
And we think you're a
policewoman.
And you're an ex-football
player?
>> No, I'm a landscaper.
>> Are you really?
>> Did Danni say something about
being a football player?
>> She said you looked familiar.
>> I wish I was.
>> Margaret was asking Gary
a question about pro football.
Who knows, watch him be retired
and he's like a
multimillionaire.
I'll kill him.
I'll freaking kill him.
>> Oh, that was good.
I needed that, man.
>> I feel so guilty, though.
>> We just got back from
the reward challenge, which
wasn't so much challenge as it
was swap up the tribes.
There's our flag right up there.
>> Hey, we have fruit.
Lookit!
Yeah!
Welcome.
Welcome, Danni.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Welcome, man.
Nice to have you guys.
You guys are tough.
>> So I was getting the feel,
you know, who they were,
showing them around the new
tribe, playing host, and being
like I'm so glad I have you
guys.
This is great.
Guys who are new to Yaxha, I'm
with you guys.
We're awesome.
We're going to win.
>> You like mad dog?
>> I haven't been tired yet.
A lot of other people in my
tribe have felt tired.
>> Don't overwork yourself,
though, dude.
We need to save ourselves for
those challenges.
>> No, you're right.
That's why you guys are winning.
>> The thing that sucks is that
there are four Nakum on our new
tribe and three Yaxha.
If it's a numbers game, they
could easily pick us off one by
one.
So I was like, Oh, my God, what
am I doing with four new people?
Is that Amy down there?
Amy, Gary, welcome back, guys.
There's water over here with the
rest of our team.
>> What?
>> Here's Johnny.
>> Hey, hey.
What's going on?
>> Get the ... out of here.
What the ... is going on?
Is this a joke?
>> We're Yaxha.
Thanks for having me.
>> Hey, what's up?
>> They switched us up.
>> I was like completely
blown away.
Hey, what's up, guys?
Hey, nice to meet you.
I'm looking at Gary.
I'm, like, we're decimated here,
decimated!
Gone!
>> Commercial real estate.
Farmer.
Waiter.
What do you do?
>> No football?
>> Landscaper.
Who did you think I was?
>> Oh, I thought you played for
Central Michigan.
>> I went to Central Michigan,
but I didn't play there.
>> No? Oh.
>> I thought Gary was gonna die
when he looked at me, because
I called him out right away
on the whole quarterback thing.
I don't know, maybe he just
doesn't want anybody to know he
was a former professional
quarterback because, you know,
you think right away, he doesn't
need the money.
>> Where you from?
>> Kansas.
>> I'm totally gonna deny
that I'm Gary Hoogebum until the
end.
I'm not going to blow my
strategy, and that's my cover.
So I'm keeping it.
>> How are you all doing?
>> Hi, guys.
>> What are you guys doing over
here?
>> There's been a little team
mix-up.
>> No way, no way.
No way.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I thought you guys
were just sitting here for a
picnic.
>> You came over and I was
like why is she so surprised.
>> I'm like, we have company.
(indistinct conversations)
>> It's all we can do, man.
You know what I'm saying?
>> They have more men.
>> With this switch-up today, I
don't feel safe at all.
Not at all.
>> Damn, this is the first time
it rained.
>> My head and my stomach
are so mixed up right now,
with everything that's
happened today, I'm trying
frantically to scramble in my
head to see, you know, what
we're going to do.
I think the old Nakum tribe,
myself, Cindy, Brooke, and Judd,
is going to stick together with
the old Nakum tribe.
But who knows what Yaxha can do?
It's still four against four.
So, food is in our belly.
There's been a major turnover,
and game is on.
(thunder rumbling)
>> I thought they were
just visiting.
>> I was just like,
whatever, man.
I don't give a crap.
>> I know I was shocked, but my
stomach is like...
>> But honestly, when I first
saw these people back at camp,
I was like, ah, whatever.
Who cares?
Tribes have been switched, man.
It's great, I love it, man.
It didn't bother me at the least
bit.
I know it bothered Margaret, and
Margaret's still walking on
eggshells, man.
I'm just glad that I'm not
involved with all those other
guys, man.
I mean, we had Bobby Jon.
We had Blake.
We had Brandon and me, which was
kind of, you know, a male
testosterone thing.
Now over here, man, I know I'm
the big gun around here, man.
I know it.
You feel like you're King Kong,
man.
Ah, feeling good, baby.
(roaring)
>> What's her name?
What's that girl...?
>> Brooke.
She's cool and everything, but
she's not an athlete.
Want to get rid of her?
>> We could try to start with
her if we had to.
They're down in numbers.
If we can keep us four tight,
we really need to.
>> I bet Brooke is better than
Lydia is at stuff.
>> I know.
But as soon as we get rid of
Lydia, if we have to, they could
get rid of us one by one.
>> I know.
>> We're going to push for
Brooke so we can keep the old
Yaxha together, just in case,
just to always have the numbers
and keep Lydia around just
because she is a hard worker.
>> Let's just let them approach
us.
>> Okay.
>> Okay? 'Cause you don't want
to be too pushy.
Because then people back away.
>> Judd told me, he goes, I'm
with you, man, he goes, I got
your back.
>> Yeah.
And Judd's from Jersey.
We know a lot of the same kind
of things.
>> We connect.
Okay, we'll see what's up.
Yeah.
>> Hey, Judd.
>> Yeah.
>> Jimmy, the first guy
that went out, threw out his
bicep?
He never got to come up here.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah, he couldn't make it up
here.
>> Who's the strongest girl?
Margaret, right?
>> Yeah, she's strong.
Cindy's tough.
>> The two weakest we see is
Brooke and Lydia.
>> Who's your strongest?
>> Who are you like tighter
with, Cindy or Margaret?
Like, if we were to like...
>> It's hard to say, you know, I
can see you guys, I'm kind of
more personable already with you
than I am with any of the girls
that I was on my team with.
I don't know.
>> Right.
>> It just didn't kind of click.
>> You know when you have like a
natural click.
>> Yeah, you can feel it.
You can see it.
It's all just natural.
>> That's what I was
saying to Jamie.
I'm obviously sticking with you.
Got to stick with the strongest.
>> I mean, I'm-- like I said,
man, I'm all with you guys, man.
If it goes this way, we get
rid of, uh, we get rid of...
>> We get rid of Brooke
and we get Lydia.
Then we can get rid of Margaret
or Cindy.
Then we've got Rafe.
Rafe will vote whatever we say
to vote.
>> Yeah, Rafe will do
whatever we do.
>> Yeah.
>> So it's kind of hard,
though, because we're still in
that newlywed type phase.
We're like...
>> Still learning.
>> You don't go a day without
talking.
>> I'm all for that, man.
Like I said, I'm basically, now,
this is the game.
The game's started.
>> Yeah.
>> Here I come, you know?
I mean, I like where I'm sitting
right now.
I feel-- feel very good, man.
Me and Stephenie and Jamie hit
it off already.
I think we got a little alliance
going.
We're not eating the peel right
now.
>> Yeah, I am.
>> Oh, you eat the peel?
I have no problem talking to my
old tribe, man.
I really don't, because I didn't
feel the love, man.
I didn't feel the love there at
all.
I felt no love there.
So they got to go, man.
They got to get out of my
jungle, man.
Get out of my jungle right away,
man-- go.
See you later.
>> This new world of mine,
I have some concerns.
I really do.
I mean, look at the tribe we
have.
Bobby Jon, Blake, Brandon,
Danni.
There's four of them and three
of us.
They're just going to pick us
off, one by one.
>> Bobby and I had a
little bathroom break, and a
little pep talk.
We were like, you know what, we
have the four on three in this
camp, we have the physical team.
When we do lose, and it is time
to vote, you know, we already
picked the order.
It's Amy, Brian, and Gary out
the door.
>> Water's warm.
Let's see.
You got a tweaker.
It's swollen.
>> Oh, my God.
I hurt my ankle going
out the first round in that
Mayan ball game.
Everybody knows I have a
sprained ankle.
I'm not sure if they know how
bad it is.
You know, I'm trying not to
wince as much around them
with everybody, but, you know,
there's some pain there.
>> You want your ankle taped?
You want it wrapped?
>> It's killing me, but the
fact that I'm not limping, yes,
it's on purpose.
I want them to think I can walk.
I just think I'm a major target
right now.
There's no doubt in my mind.
If I don't do well in the next
challenge, I'm gone.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
All right.
First things first.
Cindy, give up immunity.
So Nakum has decorated the
immunity idol.
Brian, got to be a little
irritating.
>> It's going to be a blue
feather tonight.
No problem.
>> PROBST: All right.
Let's get to today's immunity
challenge.
Here's how it works.
On my go, both tribes will
paddle out and retrieve three
tribe-colored bags.
You will then race back to
shore.
Once you're back on your mat,
untie the bags and empty them
into a basket.
Inside each bag, you'll find
Maya war clubs.
You'll then throw the clubs at
three targets which are 30, 40
and 50 feet away.
First tribe to break all three
tiles wins immunity.
Losers, Tribal Council.
Two rules.
No individual tribe member can
break more than one tile.
Second rule: if you're not
having any luck, tag out, let
somebody else take a shot.
Nakum, you have one extra
member.
You're sitting somebody out.
Who's it going to be?
>> Lydia.
>> PROBST: Lydia, take a spot on
the bench.
Everybody else, take a spot on
the start.
Wait for my go.
Here we go, guys.
For immunity, Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Push in a little bit.
>> Everybody together.
On the count of three, go.
Paddle.
All together.
>> PROBST: Both tribes paddling
very well.
>> Grab it.
>> PROBST: Yaxha at their first
bag.
Amy working on it.
Nakum at their first bag.
Rafe trying to untie it.
>> Bite it hard.
>> Pull, pull.
>> Okay, got it.
>> PROBST: Nakum has their first
bag.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Yaxha has their first
bag.
They're back in it.
It's a race to the second bag.
>> Ramming speed!
>> Paddle, paddle, paddle.
>> Paddle harder.
>> We can't.
>> Rafe, push them out of the
way.
>> Paddle, guys, we're so close
to ours.
>> PROBST: Nakum is pushing
Yaxha off the course.
Don't let them in!
Nakum at their second bag.
Yaxha in trouble.
Big advantage for Nakum.
>> Come on, guys.
>> Let's go, Bobby.
>> Everybody in, come on, go.
>> PROBST: Nakum has their
second bag, heading for their
third and final bag.
>> Don't let go.
>> Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Nakum at their third
bag now.
Yaxha has their second bag,
heading for their third and
final bag.
A lot of ground to make up.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Nakum has their third
bag, racing back to shore.
>> Everybody go.
Straight.
Go.
>> Come on.
>> Go, dig, Yaxha!
Come on.
>> Good job.
Good job.
>> Heave.
>> PROBST: Yaxha has their third
bag.
They're heading back.
>> Come on.
>> Hard, hard, everybody hard.
Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Nakum is first at the
beach.
They're racing to their mats.
Everybody got to get to the mat
before you can start untying.
Pick it up.
>> PROBST: Steph going to be the
first for Nakum.
>> Let's go, let's go.
>> PROBST: Yaxha back to shore.
>> Steph, you got it.
>> PROBST: Yaxha closing the
gap.
>> Come on, Steph.
>> Steph, get mad!
Do it, girl!
Yes!
Good job, Steph.
>> PROBST: Steph connects with
the first tile.
Judd in.
Brian going to be the first
thrower for Yaxha.
Nakum with one tile lead.
Judd going for the last target.
Going deep.
First tribe to break all three
tiles wins immunity.
>> Brian.
>> Tagging out, what?
>> PROBST: Brian switching out
with Danni.
Judd still trying to connect
with the second target for
Nakum.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Just misses.
>> Keep throwing it, momma.
>> PROBST: Danni very close.
Danni connects.
We're tied 1-1.
Blake now in.
Judd still throwing for Nakum.
>> Judd, do you want to switch
out?
Let's switch out.
>> Let me get this middle
one.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Second tile for
Yaxha.
Yaxha now in the lead.
Judd still throwing.
Brandon going for the last
target.
Judd needs to catch up.
Got to break something.
>> Judd, throw like a tomahawk.
Come on.
>> PROBST: And Judd connects.
We're tied 2-2.
Jamie in.
One tile left.
It's Brandon and Jamie going for
the last deep tile.
Brandon clips it.
No, it's not broken.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Next broken tile wins
immunity.
Losers go to Tribal Council.
Brandon just misses again for
Yaxha.
>> Oh.
Oh.
>> Come on, Brian.
Keep on popping it, Brandon.
>> PROBST: Brandon connects for
Yaxha.
Yaxha wins immunity.
(cheering)
Yaxha, immunity is yours.
I have a feeling the yellow
feathers will be coming out just
like that.
>> Immediately.
>> PROBST: Saved from Tribal
Council tonight.
Guaranteed at least one more day
out here.
Nakum, Tribal Council tonight.
New mixture of members on your
tribe should make for an
interesting afternoon.
I'll see you at Tribal.
Get in your boats.
Head on out.
>> I just don't like losing.
They think they're a better
team now and they're not.
>> I know.
>> The bottom line is it's still
going to be 7-7.
We're still even.
>> Yeah.
>> No matter what happens.
>> Someone has to go home now.
>> I know. It sucks.
>> Tonight at Tribal Council,
it's this four Nakum, four
Yaxha, going head-to-head, and
all we needed to do, our plan
since we got here was to try
to flip one of them, so we
could get a leg up.
Hopefully, it will be Judd.
We need Judd to feel comfortable
with us.
>> Right. He does, he does.
>> He can't stand Margaret or...
it seems like.
>> I have what I hope, but
I would not be surprised for one
second if it was a 4-4 tie.
>> So what we're thinking is, I
think it would be wise to keep
the majority.
At the same time I feel bad for
Lydia puts her heart and soul
into it.
>> But that's all of us,
all of us are going home.
>> You can't win the game
worried about people's feeling.
>> All of us are going to go
home broken.
>> We just had an immunity
challenge that was a really
close call and unfortunately we
lost it.
And everyone at camp seems to be
under the impression we just got
to vote the weakest person off.
>> What are you telling Judd?
>> That we want Lydia?
>> That we're voting for Lydia.
That's what we're doing.
>> First, Brooke and Cindy and I
are going to stick together.
We have to decide where Judd
stands-- how much, you know,
loyalty he has to the old Nakum
tribe.
>> So what's the word down by
the dock?
What are they talking about?
>> I'm kind of thinking that we
have to vote off whoever is the
weakest.
You know? I mean it really
sucks.
>> So, give me a name.
Who are they saying?
>> We're thinking Lydia.
Does that seem to be what
everybody else is?
>> Sounds fine with me.
Whatever you all want to do.
>> You know, I mean, I don't
want to, but...
>> I'd like old Nakum to stick
together.
I really would.
>> Okay.
>> But we've got 4-4, right?
>> Uh-huh.
>> If they vote one of us, we
vote one of them.
>> I mean, at this point, you
basically want to go for the
weakest player, I mean, and it's
I mean, Lydia and Brooke are
like this.
I mean, they're both even.
So, you know, and then what
happens is then it goes back and
forth.
I lose one, we lose one, they
lose one, we lose one, they lose
one.
>> It won't be that.
It's not going to do that.
Because they're gonna be four.
We'll be three.
They can pick us off one by one
because they'll always have
majority.
Whoever comes out with a
majority tribe tonight will have
majority all along.
>> Yeah, but listen, they don't
want to lose either, man.
They're gonna need us.
They need us bad.
They need me and you.
>> Absolutely. But...
>> They're not going to want to
get rid of me and you.
>> But they can also-- they can
also say, first, we'll start
with Brooke.
Then we'll go Cindy.
Then we'll go Margaret.
Then we'll go Judd.
That gets them into the merger,
because they can pick us off one
by one and they can use your
strength.
Because you're still not voted
off, but you're always in the
minority.
>> Well, if that's the case, of
course.
I mean, it's four against one.
>> You're up in the air?
>> Just, right now, I'm just
like whoa, you know, but you
definitely got my wheels
turning.
There's no doubt about that.
>> My biggest concern right now,
of course, is Jamie and
Stephenie not being as loyal
as they say they are.
That leaves me vulnerable.
Now they've got four against my
one here.
You know, and that's a little
scary.
>> It's freakin' hot, man.
>> In this game, you can't
trust anybody.
You can't trust anybody.
Sometimes you can't sleep at
night thinking about it.
You know, is it going to come
back and hit me in the face?
So when I go to Tribal Council,
I don't know who I'm going to
choose.
I mean, I don't know until I get
there.
I mean, that's just the way it
is.
I mean, I really-- I don't know.
>> PROBST: Welcome back to
Tribal Council.
Steph, this season in challenges
you've participated in, you're
now one for seven.
That brings your Survivor
total to four out of 21.
Maybe it's not bad luck
following Steph, but maybe Steph
is the bad luck.
>> I know.
I thought that today, too.
I was, like, is it me?
Do I just have this black cloud
that follows me around in the
game of Survivor, wherever I go?
You know, I like to think I'm
not bad luck, because that would
suck.
But for some reason, I end up on
the short side of the stick.
>> PROBST: Margaret, tell me
about the new tribe dynamics.
You guys were divided evenly.
Did you sense pairing off or
"we better stick together"?
>> There wasn't much pairing off
except on one occasion.
Judd was with Stephenie and
Jamie.
And they were... connected
pretty quickly.
>> PROBST: And did you read that
as something's going on or...
>> I hoped he was just
socializing.
And I'm still hoping that he's
just socializing.
>> PROBST: Judd, did you know
people were watching you, and
were you trying to hide it?
>> I wasn't hiding nothing.
We were just out there taking it
all in, just hanging out, having
a good time, laughing, getting
to know each other.
I mean just met them.
They just came into the tribe.
I was just kind of shooting the
breeze with them.
I mean, "Hey, what's up, man?
I'm Judd.
How you doing?"
>> PROBST: Lydia, you've been to
Tribal Council quite a few
times.
>> Three times. Too much.
>> PROBST: You feel a little
more confident now, with this
new tribe or just as vulnerable?
>> Well, Jeff, I have to say
that, you know, I do feel
a little bit vulnerable.
It's a new tribe.
They don't know me.
They don't know my strength yet,
you know.
I just have to put faith in them
and see what they think about
me.
But all in all, you know, I'm
not ready to leave, so...
>> PROBST: Brooke, what
specifically worries you
tonight?
>> I feel like if you have the
brute strength, you're safe on
your team, because it's about
winning the immunity challenges
right now, and so I feel, in
some ways, that the women are a
little bit more vulnerable than
the men at this point.
>> PROBST: Judd, in your
profession, you deal with all
different kinds of people every
day.
How important is that in this
game, to be able to read people,
make a decision, and be right?
>> Oh, it's very important.
I mean, I know who I connect
with right away.
That's just the way I am.
Somebody's looking at me, I can
tell right away, wow, man, I got
a connection to you, and we
definitely have something in
common.
I mean, you know, it's easy.
I can really pick people off
like that.
>> PROBST: Okay.
It is time to vote.
Brooke, you're up.
>> Lydia, I think you're one of
the hardest workers around camp,
but I'm just making this vote
based on the decision that we
need to win immunity challenges.
>> Brooke, you're an awesome
person, but this vote is for
strategy tonight.
If you go, I have a chance to go
a lot further.
I'm sorry.
>> Lydia, I have tribe
loyalties.
I gave Brooke my word, and I
won't go back.
Good luck.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Lydia.
Brooke.
One vote Brooke, one vote Lydia.
Lydia.
Two votes Lydia, one vote
Brooke.
Lydia.
That's three votes Lydia.
Brooke.
Two votes Brooke, three votes
Lydia.
Brooke.
We're tied.
Three votes Brooke, three votes
Lydia.
That's four votes Brooke, three
votes Lydia, one vote left.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala, Brooke.
You need to bring me your torch.
Brooke, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Tribal lines and personal
loyalties are going to shift
throughout this game.
Just remember, every time you
shift, you make it harder to
trust.
Grab your torches.
Go back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Judd is on the defensive.
>> It doesn't work like that.
We're all here to win a million
dollars.
>> He's a traitor.
>> It's every man for himself
out here.
>> PROBST: Cultures clash at
Yaxha.
>> I'm not a religious person.
But it would be stupid to say,
you know what, guys, I don't
want to thank Jesus for this
meal thing.
>> Lydia gets wacky.
>> I'm the queen. Whoo! Shut up.
>> Even though I've only gotten
to be out here for 11 days, I
did so much stuff that I never
thought I'd be able to do.
I think I proved myself going
through the 11-mile jungle trek.
But I don't think my new team
members got to see that.
So I didn't get a longer chance
out here to prove how strong I
am. I want to wish the girls
from my original team good luck.
You guys are some of the