>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: Margaret's negativity
was weighing on Nakum.
>> She just can't grasp the fact
that the old tribe ain't coming
back.
>> PROBST: At the challenge,
tribes learned they would
compete for hamburgers and beer.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: But they also learned
that things were shaking up.
Tonight, both tribes are
going to Tribal Council, both
tribes are voting somebody out.
In addition, to the barbecue
feast, the winning tribe earns
the right to compete in another
challenge for individual
immunity.
Survivors, ready... go!
The challenge was grueling, and
the tribes were pushed to their
limits.
Amy was down with a serious
ankle injury.
Amy is hurt.
And tempers flared when Jamie
and Bobby Jon squared off.
( both yelling )
In the end, Nakum claimed the
award.
And they have it!
Nakum wins barbecue feast and a
shot at individual immunity.
Survivors, ready.
Go!
Rafe won the challenge.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Rafe wins immunity.
And was the only person to be
safe for one more night.
>> Great stuff!
>> PROBST: At Yaxha, Brian tried
to rally Amy and Gary to oust
Bobby Jon.
>> PROBST: But both he and Amy
were also at risk.
>> Amy and Brian are probably in
the biggest threat of getting
voted off.
You know, they are probably the
physically weaker players.
>> PROBST: Over at Nakum the
tribe indulged.
>> I've never had a hamburger
taste like this.
>> It doesn't get better than
this.
>> PROBST: But Judd drank
himself into trouble.
>> Rafe, you sure you don't want
that beer?
>> There's only two beers left.
>> I definitely got one coming,
without a doubt.
>> Judd's got to watch his
mouth.
He gets so pumped up, and his
mouth works before his brain
does.
>> PROBST: During Tribal
Council, Judd turned up the heat
when he attacked Margaret.
>> Did you or did you not-- as
soon as you saw me, did you tell
me that I had A.D.D.
>> This is what it is like to
try to talk to him.
>> You should just shut up.
>> PROBST: Judd got his way and
Margaret was voted out of the
tribe.
Margaret, the tribe has spoken.
Rafe sat in on Yaxha's Tribal
Council, where Brian was voted
out.
Brian, the tribe has spoken.
Eleven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( theme song playing )
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
( crickets chirping )
>> Oh, God! Thank the Lord, man.
Listen, I want to thank you guys
too, for, you know, my bark
ain't as big as my bite, man.
And that's damn true, man, you
know.
>> We went over to Tribal
Council tonight and Margaret got
voted out; thank God, man.
She just pushed my button, man.
And she pushed it, and pushed it
and pushed it, and pushed it,
and kept pushing it.
I couldn't take it anymore.
So I kind of had a little
outburst and put her in her
place, man.
See, in the other tribe she was
the mom over there.
Everybody used to run around and
call her mom.
When she didn't have that role
any more, man, that just
devastated her.
>> I'm just glad this is all
over with.
>> I'm not a loose canon.
I mean, I blew up; but around
camp, I never do that, man.
I'm happy all day.
I'm just a big teddy bear, man,
you know.
Hopefully, I'll be laughing my
ass to the bank, and she'll
still be at home, making chicken
wings or something.
Somebody is going to badmouth
me, man-- listen, I'm not gonna
to sit there like a little wuss
and take it.
I don't care.
I ain't going to get up and hit
you either, though.
>> The thing is with Judd, he
has a big voice, you know, he's
a big guy.
So that scares a lot of people,
but it doesn't make me nervous.
If anything, it makes me want to
keep Judd closer, because I
could take him to final, and
then I would have all the votes
and Judd wouldn't have any
because he is going to keep
blowing up.
>> It's so cold.
>> This will hurt.
( tearing sound )
( exhales sharply )
That really hurt.
>> I hurt my shoulders pushing
the big ball, during the
challenge, but that's just a
part of the game.
Everybody over here at Yaxha has
these things all over them.
Um, I just got a couple of bad
ones, and I got one on my right
shoulder right now.
It is pretty bad.
I went to take my shirt off this
morning, and it was literally
pasted to it.
Got a long way to go in the
game, so I will probably get a
lot more banged up than this.
So, just right now you just be
tough and know that there is a
gold rush waiting at the end of
the rainbow.
>> Oh, man. That's disgusting.
I don't look like that, right?
>> They don't look like this.
They look like that one right
there.
>> They do?
>> Yeah.
You got one on your chin, and
one right there, and then a few
dots right there.
It makes you look tough, I
think.
>> Yeah, you like that?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> All right.
>> I have open, festering sores,
and it sucks.
I go into these challenges and
you completely forget about
this.
I probably won't even feel it.
>> PROBST: Come on in, Nakum!
Yaxha, come on in!
Both tribes getting their first
look at the new tribes after the
last Tribal Council.
Margaret voted out of Nakum.
Brian voted out at Yaxha.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge
will require team work and a lot
of dexterity.
Four tribe members are going to
wrap 30 feet of material around
their bodies, and then unspool
that material as they make their
way down field to the finish.
Here is how it works:
First person will move around a
pole as quickly as they can,
unspooling the material off of
the pole and onto their body.
You'll then move to the second
person.
You'll connect to the second
person, then together the two of
you will move around the pole,
putting the material around both
of your bodies.
Then the third person, finally
the fourth person.
So you will end up with four
people wrapping material around
the group.
Once you have all the material
around all four people, you
start moving down field and
begin unwinding the material off
of your body.
Each time a person unwinds, they
unclip, and head to the finish
mat.
There is one other person in
this challenge.
They are the winder.
Their job is to assist the other
four anyway they can by helping
them move around the pole or
helping them keep their balance.
First tribe to get all five
tribe members to the finish mat
wins a reward.
Want to know what are you
playing for?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Well, the Maya are
credited with a few things.
Relationship with the stars,
accounting system, Mayan
calendar, but there is one big
discovery you might not be
familiar with: the Maya
discovered chocolate.
Most would agree it might be
their biggest discovery.
Today you are playing for
chocolate.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Also, the winning
tribe will get a chance to take
part in a zip-line canopy tour
of the jungles of Guatemala.
You will literally glide over
these jungles.
When you're finished, chocolate
feast awaits you.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Nakum you have one
extra member.
You're sitting somebody out?
>> Judd.
>> PROBST: Judd's going to sit
this one out.
Give you a minute to figure out
who is going to be the winder
and who are going to be the four
"wind-ees."
Then we'll get started.
All right, everybody is at a
pole, clipped in, ready to go.
Amy is the winder for Yaxha;
Jamie, the winder for Nakum.
Here we go, for a reward.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Got to tag before you can start
winding.
Jamie's there first.
There's Amy, on the bad ankle.
>> Wait, wait, wait.
>> PROBST: You're wrapping the
material around your body.
>> Come on, Steph.
Come on.
>> Keep spinning, baby.
>> Come on, Brandon.
Come on, come on.
>> PROBST: Steph unclips.
Clipping in to Lydia.
Now the two of them have to wrap
the material around both bodies.
Brandon and Amy now back in it.
Brandon clips in to Gary.
The two of them now have to move
that material around both of
their bodies.
>> Back it up.
>> Steph and Lydia having a lot
of trouble at their second pole.
Get together, hug.
Now you got it going.
>> Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: Gary and Brandon with
a lead for Yaxha now, working
together well.
>> You got the lead, just don't
mess up.
>> PROBST: Steph and Lydia have
a lot of time to make up.
Gary and Brandon moving up to
Bobby Jon.
>> Take your time.
>> PROBST: Gary, Brandon, Bobby
Jon got a decent lead.
Big reward at stake.
Nakum making up some time.
Both tribes at the third pole.
>> Spin, Bobby Jon.
No, spin your body.
>> PROBST: Yaxha seems to be
slowing down.
Nakum making up a lot of ground.
>> Keep going, keep going.
>> Stop right here, right here.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, Gary,
Brandon, unclip and move to the
fourth pole.
Danni clips in.
Yaxha must now wrap the material
around all four tribe members.
Nakum, you're still in it.
Keep moving, let's go.
>> Move those feet, Lydia.
Keep it going.
You guys can do it.
We're still in it.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Nakum heading to the
fourth pole.
>> Go to your right, Brandon.
There we go.
>> Keep going, you got it, you
got it, you got it.
>> PROBST: It's getting tougher
to move with four people.
>> Keep your hands up.
>> PROBST: Keep your hands up.
That's it, Nakum; that's
working.
We're at the fourth pole, and we
are dead even.
Nakum has made up some time.
>> We got it, we got it.
We're beating them.
We got it.
>> Here we go, here we go.
>> PROBST: Nakum is good.
Jamie, you're done.
Nakum is unwinding.
>> One more round.
Come on!
>> PROBST: Jamie's first to hit
the mat.
( all shouting )
Amy, you're done.
Yaxha is unwinding.
Working hard, making up a lot of
ground.
Nakum seems to be slowing down.
Now Yaxha is back in the lead.
>> Come on Yaxha.
>> PROBST: Nakum, don't panic;
patience is key.
Danni's out of it, heads to the
finish.
Cindy is out of it.
Nakum takes a tumble.
Bobby Jon is out.
Nakum panicking, cannot get up.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Gary and Brandon with
a big lead for Yaxha now.
Nakum really falling behind.
Gary unclipped.
Rafe right behind,
not giving up.
Brandon is the last one!
>> Come on!
Yeah!
>> PROBST: Yaxha wins reward!
( cheering )
Yaxha, good work.
You remained calm.
Big reward.
Chocolate, zip-line canopy tour.
You are leaving from here, going
to that right now.
Nakum, flip side: you fell down;
you couldn't get up; you guys
panicked.
I got nothing for you.
Head on back to camp.
>> This is crazy.
>> I'm afraid of heights.
>> We won a reward challenge
today.
We really needed some momentum
on our side, and we got it.
Just to get out of camp and come
and do something new is just
amazing.
>> I'm petrified right now.
The zip line-- you have this
harness thing on.
You buckle into this big cable.
Jump.
And you're up high, which, of
course, I'm afraid of heights.
What happens if I get stuck in
the middle?
>> You won't.
>> I won't?
>> No.
>> You're just hanging there,
and you just have all your
confidence in the cable line.
It's a little frightening.
>> I'm going alone, right?
>> You got it.
( crying )
You're good.
>> Oh, my God.
I can't believe this.
>> There you go.
Yeah.
Woo!
( monkey howling )
Oh, my God!
>> Way to go, Amy!
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Freakin' get me there!
>> Whoo!
>> Good job, Amy.
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, my God, are we done?
An unbelievable experience.
But probably, for me, just a
once-in-a-lifetime experience.
>> Yeah, Bobby Jon.
>> We got to swing through the
jungle on these cables, and it
felt just, just majestic...
Going through the jungle, the
wind hitting your face and just
looking at all these tall plants
and trees and stuff.
Woo!
That stuff I see in the movies,
you know?
I've never done anything like
that in my entire life before.
I'll probably never do it again.
>> Oh, man, this is going to be
cool.
>> Woo!
Woo!
>> Oh, man!
>> Man, I had no idea that you
could even do that.
Just flying through the air
and...
God, it was so cool.
My God!
Holy cow, man!
( laughter )
Look at all that stuff.
Oh, my God.
At the end of the zip line was
the most chocolate I've ever
seen in my life.
I mean, it was a chocolate-fest.
Cake, pralines, cookies,
strawberries-- I mean, you name
it, it was there.
Cheers on a good win today.
>> Yes, absolutely.
Great win.
>> Momentum.
>> Oh, my God, cherries!
>> Holy cow, man.
That's a good piece of cake.
>> So much chocolate.
>> Man, I pigged out.
I mean, I have never pigged
out on chocolate that much,
ever.
Just looking at the muddy
ground-- 'cause it looks, you
know, like chocolate almost a
little bit-- makes me a little
bit sick.
So do we want to try and take
all this or just?
>> Take the whole thing.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm going to remember today
for two reasons.
The day I went rip-cording
through a jungle, and the day
that I ate the most chocolate
I have ever eaten in my entire
life.
>> God, I hope I hold that down.
>> What do you guys want to
play?
>> We'll play UNO.
>> I always try to do like
different things around camp
that will help us have fun and
pass time.
King is reverse.
Queen is skip.
We picked all these little
leaves from the tree and then
painted four different suits and
all the cards, so it made a deck
of 52 cards, with even two
jokers.
>> The stems are the bottom of
the cards, Amy.
>> Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Today happens to be my
birthday, so we thought we'd go
over and invite Nakum over for a
little pool party.
>> Skip me?
>> No, it skipped you and me.
>> Skip to me.
>> Nakum!
Nakum!
>> Guys, I think the other tribe
is coming to visit.
>> I think the other tribe is
here.
>> They yelled it twice.
>> I heard "Nakum."
You guys going down there?
>> Yeah, let's go.
>> Nakum!
>> That is them.
That's them.
>> Probably out there on the
boat.
>> Why are they coming here?
There is nothing to do here.
>> I don't know, maybe they came
to invite us to their pool.
>> I ain't going to their pool.
>> These are our enemies at this
point.
>> Yeah, but this has never
happened.
>> We were like, should we go?
I was like, yeah, let's walk
down.
And then Jamie started saying,
I think it's a bad idea.
I don't think we should do this.
I was like, guys, what's the
worst thing that is going to
happen?
>> Oh, there they are.
>> Yo!
>> Judd the stud.
>> Hi!
It's my birthday, so we figured
we would invite you all over for
a pool party.
>> Oh, what are you guys up to,
man?
>> What's going on?
>> We just wanted to come show
some love.
>> We have a few little bitty
birthday treats.
>> I'll go.
>> All right, let's get on.
>> Come on, let's go.
Let's get our boat.
Man, let's have a party.
Danni's birthday today, man.
>> We really just wanted to have
a party.
I mean, we have been here 17
days now, and I'm always big on
birthday parties, so we had to
do something.
>> I don't like these people, so
I don't understand why we're
going over to hang out.
>> I'm with you, man.
>> I'm right there with you.
>> I didn't want to go.
I thought it was stupid.
It's a long way.
It's hot, and I just found it
unnecessary.
Why should we go and hang out
with the people that we want to
get rid of?
But, you know, I have to show an
interest in what the tribe wants
to do, so I went.
>> Amy, hey, how you doing?
>> This is nice.
>> What's up, guys?
>> That's nice.
>> How you doing?
>> What's up, man?
>> You guys should sleep out
there.
>> We thought about it.
>> We've got some chocolate.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> How do you have extra
chocolate?
>> Are you serious?
>> Thank you.
Oh, my...
>> Happy birthday.
Thank you.
>> How old are you?
>> This is all for us?
>> Oh, thank you guys so much.
>> Oh, my God, the chocolate.
Like, that was the main reason I
was coming.
They said they had chocolate
for us.
I was like, hell, yeah, I will
go in your pool, and I'll eat
your chocolate.
It was unreal.
>> Unbelievable.
>> That is so good.
>> Aah! Man!
>> Thank you for the invitation.
>> Absolutely.
>> Today is just about a
fellowship.
We're coming together.
I mean, the chief of the tribes
in ancient Mayan times would go
and communicate with each other.
They would sit and they would
smoke, and they would be at war
later on.
>> This is like heaven.
I would just sit here all day.
>> We're not getting out until
we leave, man.
>> Woo!
This is paradise.
>> How old is your oldest
brother?
Mine is 39.
>> I was being quiet.
I was figuring everybody out,
whether Amy and Gary were with
them, or were they waiting for a
merge to try and get back with
us.
I was worried that maybe
Stephanie was getting along too
well with other people.
Maybe she would, you know, form
bonds there.
I'm here for business, and
everyone else should be also.
>> We can go now.
>> Thanks for having us.
>> Thank you so much for the
chocolate, you guys.
>> Thank you for inviting us.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Thank you so much.
Jamie is like, hey guys, are you
guys ready? Out of nowhere.
He's like, I think we should
leave soon, and he's like, no, I
kind of want to go now.
>> You are so shady.
>> You are like the shadiest
person.
>> My being quiet?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, I don't care.
I'll like those people after
this game is over, you know.
I think we stayed too long,
because it's getting way too
friendly over here.
It's kind of making me sick,
they were all getting along
so well.
>> I'm still sticking to the
game plan we got, though.
>> Well, we have to.
>> No, I'm not going to stick to
the game plan because we went to
a pool party.
>> Hey, y'all can vote my ass
out if you all want to.
>> Jamie, what is wrong with
you?
>> You said I was being shady.
>> You are, I think you are
losing it in Guatemala.
>> Jamie sometimes, like, freaks
me out.
I just don't understand where
the kid's head is at sometimes.
I'm not going to back down to
somebody like him.
So there could be a clashblac
between he and I, because I,
can't take it.
>> These things are eating this
stuff.
I almost caught one in my mouth.
>> I think we're going to win
immunity because we have good
momentum.
And you know what, when we win
immunity, we could have options.
If we don't win immunity, we're
going to have to be for
ourselves, right?
>> It's you or me.
Those three are tight.
>> Right now, there's five of us
in the Yaxha tribe.
Three original Nakum members,
and then Amy and myself, who was
originally Yaxha.
So Brandon, Danni and Bobby Jon
I think were tight when they
came over here.
They might be leaning towards
Amy.
So Amy is vulnerable if we lose
our next immunity.
>> If we don't freakin' win
immunity, right...
I'll be honest, I'm not going to
lie about anything, I'm just
going to sell myself.
You can lie.
>> I can lie.
>> But I'll kick your ass
afterwards.
I'm going to find you in
Michigan.
I'll put in Gary Hawkins, 46.
It'll come, bing, bing, bing.
Cell phones, address, maps.
I'll call the locals over there.
You can give me the lowdown on
Mr. Gary Hawkins,
ex-professional football player.
>> Ex-professional, yeah, I
wish.
>> Yeah.
If you are and I find out after,
I'm going to beat you down like
a stepchild.
>> What do you want me to do?
>> I'm going to beat you...
'cause, I don't care.
>> I know, can I make something
up?
>> I want people to give me
their word.
So I hope Gary doesn't
disappoint me.
If Gary is playing me, I'm going
to kick his ass.
I'm going to kick his ass.
>> Let's just not lose the
immunity, so you don't have to
cut my throat.
I'm trying to keep a straight
face.
I'm trying not to let her read
me, because she thinks she can
read people so well.
But, uh, she'll never find Gary
Hawkins in Grand Haven because
there is no such thing as a Gary
Hawkins in Grand Haven.
So she could be searching for
years.
>> "The history of the ancients
in this place have been
revealed.
Archaeologists unearthed the
mysteries, but still secrets are
concealed.
So you'll have to do some
digging to excavate the clues,
fail to put them together first
and one more tribe mate you will
lose."
Right now, it's a numbers game.
We need to win this challenge as
a tribe, so if there were a
merge, we've five on five.
>> Are you nervous?
>> In a good way.
>> Yeah, anxious.
>> I'm glad I'm in there.
If we don't win, and if we do
merge, we're going to be in a
mess.
We're going to be out-numbered
by two people, and they are just
going to pick us right off.
Today's the biggest day ever.
Bigger than any reward we're
going to see.
Bigger than anything for this
tribe.
I mean, this is it.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, shall we get to
today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity,
back up for grabs.
Today's immunity challenge will
test your ability to work
together as a team while solving
a puzzle.
Here is how it will work:
Three members from each tribe
are responsible for retrieving
giant puzzle pieces from the
sand pit.
On my go, one at a time, you'll
run out, attempting to find a
piece.
Each time you find a piece, you
bring it back, drop it in front
of your mat, and the next person
goes out.
Each person has to make at least
one attempt.
After that, go in any order you
choose.
Once you have collected all 12
pieces, two different tribe
members will race to assemble
the puzzle.
It resembles the Maya calendar.
First tribe to get it together
correctly wins immunity and a
one-in-ten-shot at a million
bucks.
Losers, Tribal Council, somebody
going home.
Nakum, you have one extra
member, you're sitting somebody
out.
Judd sat out the last challenge;
he cannot sit out this one.
>> Lydia.
>> PROBST: Lydia's going to sit
out.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, running for Yaxha, it
is Brandon, Bobby Jon and Danni.
Running for Nakum: Jamie, Judd,
Cindy.
Here we go.
For immunity, Survivors, ready?
Go!
Brandon and Jamie first into the
sand.
Both quickly get the first
pieces.
>> Good job, Jamie!
>> PROBST: Judd and Bobby Jon
coming back with the second
pieces for both tribes.
Cindy is the first to start
digging.
Danni trying to find a piece she
can handle.
Cindy has got a piece.
They're heavy with that sand.
>> Good job, Cindy.
>> Good job. Good job.
>> PROBST: Cindy dragging back
the third puzzle piece for
Nakum.
Jamie back out.
>> Keep digging, keep digging.
>> PROBST: Danni found a piece,
but she can't lift it.
>> Tag out, Danni.
>> PROBST: Danni gives up.
Brandon back out.
Jamie with the fourth puzzle
piece for Nakum.
Nakum four, Yaxha two.
Brandon coming back with the
third piece for Yaxha.
Judd with the fifth piece
for Nakum.
>> Way to go, Judd.
>> PROBST: Nakum leads 5-3.
Cindy back out in the sand.
Bobby Jon, man-handling a huge
piece for Yaxha.
That's four for Yaxha.
There are only buried pieces
left.
Both tribes are going to have to
dig now.
>> Come on, Cindy.
Good job, Cindy.
There you go.
>> PROBST: Brandon back with
another piece for Yaxha.
Tied, five each.
Cindy with the sixth piece for
Nakum.
Jamie back out.
( grunting )
Bobby Jon has another piece.
Both tribes now with six puzzle
pieces.
Danni has unearthed one.
>> PROBST: Danni coming back
with the seventh piece for
Yaxha.
Brandon back out.
>> Come on, Jamie!
>> PROBST: Brandon has the
eighth piece for Yaxha.
Jamie back with the seventh
piece for Nakum.
Bobby Jon, searching but not
finding anything.
>> Come on, brother!
Faster!
Judd with the eighth piece for
Nakum.
Jamie back out.
Bobby Jon has another piece.
Yaxha with nine pieces, Nakum
with eight.
Jamie has another piece for
Nakum.
We are tied, both tribes with
nine.
Danni with the tenth piece for
Yaxha.
Yaxha has two pieces left;
Nakum has three.
Judd and Brandon on top of each
other.
Judd has a big piece.
And it's for Nakum.
>> Keep digging, Brandon.
>> PROBST: Both tribes with ten
pieces.
Hard to find those last pieces
in all that sand.
Brandon, still looking.
>> Jamie, over to your left,
right down there.
>> PROBST: Jamie has another
piece for Nakum.
>> Right here, Jamie.
Right here.
Jamie just threw the piece right
into Steph's shin.
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: Nakum with one piece
left.
Yaxha with two pieces left.
>> I can't find it.
Cindy searching for that last
Nakum puzzle piece.
>> Come on, Cindy.
Cindy with the 12th piece for
Nakum.
Nakum is finished.
Nakum can now begin assembling
the puzzle.
Steph and Rafe go to work.
>> Come on, Brandon!
>> PROBST: Brandon with the 11th
piece for Yaxha.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Yaxha has one piece
left; Nakum already started
putting the puzzle together.
Bobby Jon, searching for that
last puzzle piece.
Yaxha falling behind.
>> Keep going, Bobby Jon.
>> I got it, I got it.
>> Okay, hurry, hurry.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon with the
final piece for Yaxha.
Gary and Amy, starting to put
the puzzle together.
>> There you go.
>> Good job, Yaxha.
>> PROBST: They've got some time
to make up.
Remaining calm will be the key
to this.
>> Let's see this one.
>> PROBST: Steph and Rafe with a
big advantage for Nakum.
Gary and Amy trying to catch up.
>> That one, right there.
>> Good job, Gary.
>> PROBST: Gary with another
piece for Yaxha.
Nakum making a lot of progress,
puzzle coming together nicely.
>> Yeah, good one.
Yeah.
>> This piece I think goes over
there.
>> There you go.
>> Great, just leave it there.
>> PROBST: Nakum getting closer
and closer.
Yaxha is not that far behind.
>> That one goes right there.
>> PROBST: Very close.
Very close.
>> Help me out, help me out.
>> PROBST: Nakum stuck with
their last few pieces.
Yaxha with only four pieces left
You guys are very close.
You got to move, Gary!
You got to move Amy!
Nakum may have figured it out.
And they have!
Nakum wins immunity!
>> Yes!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Nakum, unlike in the
reward challenge, you worked
well together this time.
You did not panic.
Immunity is yours; no Tribal
Council tonight.
( cheering )
Yaxha, sadly, for one of you,
day 18 will be your last.
Tribal Council tonight, somebody
going home.
Head on back to camp.
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> It's a devastating loss.
It's a loss for my tribe, and
it's a loss for myself.
I knew going into this, if we
didn't win immunity, I felt that
I had an uphill battle, like I
had that feeling.
>> The one thing, you know, if I
were you, I'd mention to Bobby
Jon and Brandon, there will be a
merge soon, I would think so.
Thing is Danni, I probably could
never outlast anybody here,
or outplay anybody here.
But the biggest attribute that I
can possibly bring, to the
people left here, is to outwit
people.
There is no one better on this
island right here.
>> You know, I would hate to
vote Bobby Jon out, because last
time he didn't get to go to the
merge, you know?
But that's like with anybody,
nobody's had the chance to go.
>> Is that an option?
>> I don't know.
Not going to be asking somebody
like me back.
>> I thought that wasn't fair at
all for both of them to come
back, because it's such a big
advantage for the two of them.
>> The fact that you just said
that, opens another door.
But we bring somebody else with
us.
Could be Gary.
>> When Danni mentioned Bobby
Jon's name, I said, there is my
angle.
Nobody wants to vote anybody
off, but Bobby Jon has been here
two times in a row, so I'm
thinking if I can get Gary to do
it and then we get Danni, you
know, that's my last shot,
basically.
>> Danni brought up Bobby Jon's
name.
>> Well, here's the deal.
Danni and Brandon are running
the show.
>> You're right.
>> Okay, and if they are looking
for loyalty, I got to show to
them loyalty.
If they decide to go with Bobby
Jon, I am with them.
Danni's your play.
>> I know, but do I have you?
>> If you got Danni, you got me.
>> My angle right now is Gary.
And I got to hope on Danni.
Hopefully, there will be three
votes for Bobby Jon.
It will be a miracle, but I have
had miracles in the past, so I
won't be giving up on that.
( thunder rumbles )
>> This feels worse than it felt
in Palau, right now.
>> What, the nervousness or?
>> I'm just so close, man,
you know, but you just ain't
there, and getting close.
This situation doesn't count.
You know, I might get voted out
tonight.
I'm going to feel real, real bad
off if I don't make... make the
jury.
But you know what?
That's life, bro.
>> I want to make it to the
jury.
To me that would be a lifelong
dream come true.
>> Nobody gets second chances.
And I have been given one,
and I just don't want to blow
it.
( thunder rumbles )
>> This is definitely the
hardest decision, and I want to
make sure we're all together on
everything.
Hey, cowboys.
I don't want any of them to
go home.
And, um... I don't know what to
do.
>> God, I was... hoping it
wouldn't come to this, you know?
>> Yeah.
Bobby Jon and Stephanie had a
chance to play this game before,
and none of us have.
>> Yeah, like, she is probably
more deserving being here than
Bobby Jon, and that's what has
been getting to me, you know?
Because you form alliances and
then you end up voting out
people that may deserve to be
here more than other people that
are in your alliance.
>> Right.
>> I'm somewhat conflicted
because here I have my alliance
with Bobby Jon and everything,
but I believe that these other
people, you know, Gary and Amy,
maybe, deserve to be here a
little bit more than he does
because he has already had his
shot.
This is probably the most
complicated spot I have been in
the game, and it's really taking
a toll on my mind.
You getting that rain past us?
I mean, it doesn't say in
Survivor rules' that you have t
deceive, manipulate, cheat.
You don't even have to make
alliances.
You are doing this stuff, why?
So you can get one step closer
to a million dollars, and it's
like you're selling your soul or
something.
>> PROBST: So, Danni, Day 18,
seven people are gone, you're
still here.
It's got to feel fairly good at
this point.
>> Well, nothing feels really
good today.
I mean, to have to come to
Tribal Council tonight because
we've all bonded so well, it
sucks.
>> PROBST: Gary, what is
different today than was
different the last time you guys
came to Tribal Council?
>> I think this group that we
have here is so tight just
because the energy, the attitude
and how close we have gotten
after competing as hard as we
can and going through some tough
times and going through some
great times.
>> PROBST: Amy, how would you
characterize this experience so
far, 18 days in?
>> This is the bomb, right here.
I went through things that I
will never experience anywhere
else, you know?
You get to know these people.
You go through tough times and
you bond together.
I mean, I love these guys.
>> PROBST: Brandon, when you
come to Tribal Council, you are
voting someone out.
You are sending them home.
It's over, torch out, bye-bye.
>> As ugly as that.
>> PROBST: How much more
difficult is that for you than
you anticipated?
>> It's a lot more difficult
than I anticipated.
The hardest part is justifying
why you voted them out.
Everything comes into
consideration.
You're like, okay, okay, I made
alliances, and this person is
not my alliance, got to vote
them out.
On the other hand, you think
maybe a person in your alliance
may not be as deserving to stay
in this game, I mean, really
shouldn't you keep the person
that is deserving?
>> PROBST: Danni, did you
anticipate this dilemma of
"deserving" because of how they
play versus "deserving" because
I gave them the word?
>> Oh, I mean, yeah, I know that
is how it goes.
I feel it is just part of the
game.
But giving your word and keeping
it sometimes is going to be hard
in this game.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, what do
you do when you come to Tribal
Council and you don't want to
vote anybody out?
Do you look at every person and
say they are valuable, or is it
simply alliances, what is it?
>> My only answer would be what
kind of deal did you make with
somebody on day two, on day
three, on day four.
For Bobby Jon, that's the only
answer I have.
I don't know about the other
guys, but that's my answer.
>> PROBST: Well, right or wrong,
it is time to vote.
Bobby Jon, you are up.
>> You know, Amy, you're the
strongest, most real human being
I have ever met in my entire
life, my entire life.
I won't ever meet anybody more
real than you, ever.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Amy.
Bobby Jon.
One vote: Amy; one vote: Bobby
Jon.
Amy-- that's two Amy.
>> Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala: Amy.
That's three and that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Play cool, guys.
>> PROBST: Amy, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, I am convinced after
tonight's Tribal Council that
you really have become a close
group, and, hopefully, that will
help you because you are about
to embark on a new challenge.
The four of you will not go back
to your camp.
You will go directly to Nakum's
camp.
You and Nakum are no longer two
tribes; you're going to merge
into one new tribe.
All of your personal items, all
the rewards you've won will be
relocated.
These are your new buffs.
You guys are responsible for
taking these buffs, delivering
them, handing them out.
And the ten of you need to
decide on a new tribe name.
Whole new game.
Grab your torches, head out.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on Survivor
Nakum awakes to a big surprise.
>> What's going on?
What happened?
>> Merge, baby, merge.
>> PROBST: The Survivors must
choose their fate.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: And tempers flare at
the new tribe.
>> I don't care what you do.
>> Dude, shut up, man.
Shut up, man. I can't listen to
you right now.
>> I'm very proud of myself
getting this far.
You look down at your soul here
out in Guatemala.
You have absolutely nothing, and
I have learned a tremendous
amount of things I never knew
about myself, and I will
continue to learn about myself
after this journey is over, when
I get home. I made some
great friends, and I had a great
time, and, uh, I wouldn't want