>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor: Gary tried to lure
Lydia away from the Alliance of
Five.
>> But Judd was listening in.
>> I hear Gary working all over
Lydia, man.
Her eyes are bulging out of her
head.
"Yeah, Gary."
>> I have to cover my own ass,
so if somebody approach me with
a better deal, I'm going with
it.
>> JEFF: At the reward
challenge, the shift in loyalty
was exposed when Lydia helped
remove Stephenie from the game.
Steph not happy at all with
that, Lydia.
>> I haven't eaten.
Steph ate three times.
>> So did Gary.
So did Danni.
>> JEFF: And Cindy smashed her
way to victory.
>> Cindy!
>> JEFF: Cindy chose Rafe to
join her on the hot springs
waterfall reward.
>> You know, Cindy and I are
kind of in this together for
better or for worse.
This was, like, the best day.
>> JEFF: Back at camp, with
Lydia on board, Gary and Danni
concocted a plan to approach
Rafe to join them in an
alliance.
>> JEFF: But Danni was
strategically keeping her
options open.
>> I've got to look at who is in
control of the game and play up
to it 'cause I'm not going to
go home.
>> JEFF: At the immunity
challenge, Gary and Rafe were
neck and neck, but it was Rafe
who won immunity.
Once again, Rafe wins immunity!
Before Tribal Council, Gary had
the opportunity to make his move
with Rafe.
>> Rafe told me that he didn't
trust Judd, so at some point,
they're going to turn on each
other.
>> At Tribal Council, Gary
exposed Judd's lie about the
hidden idol.
>> He goes, "Okay, I'll tell
you.
It's on the ground."
Well, I followed them out in
the woods the next day, and the
idol was in the tree.
>> JEFF: You got caught.
You got outed tonight for lying.
>> Okay, all right.
I lied about the damn idol.
>> JEFF: But despite Gary's
efforts, his tribe considered
him too much of a threat.
Rafe stuck with his alliance,
and even Danni and Lydia helped
vote Gary out.
Six are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Well, last night at Tribal
Council, Gary got voted out,
and, uh, now that there's six of
us left, I'm next on the totem
pole, you know?
About ready to have my head
chopped off.
>> I was awake.
I was not delirious or anything,
dreaming.
I smelled sausage and eggs.
I really did.
>> Well, if you smelled bacon
and eggs or sausage and eggs,
Lyd, it's probably, uh, Steph
farting again.
So that could be a little bit of
a problem.
>> No, I went to the bathroom.
No more gas.
>> You know, usually when you
got, like, that egg smell...
>> Egg smell.
>> First thing in the
morning, they're not eggs, man.
>> It's funny how everybody
tries to play it off like
nothing happened when we just
had this heated Tribal Council
last night, you know, how
there's been a lot of lying.
And I think it's 'cause they're
all scared.
I mean, after everything's been
called out into the open, I just
kind of sit back last night, and
I'm like, "These people are
unbelievable."
I have a feeling who's going to
win this one.
>> Style.
>> That's your style, right?
You're up.
>> Is it my turn?
>> Oh!
>> Wow!
>> Whoo!
>> Spunky.
>> That was pretty, man.
>> I think Judd's was better.
>> I'm definitely not going to
go down without a fight.
>> I mean, I'm going to work
something out.
I mean, I know Lydia-- she feels
like she's on the outs now with
this group, and so I know she's
definitely in with me.
And I think it would take one
more person, um, maybe, to-to
throw something.
Ooh, my shoe.
(grunts)
This perfect little alliance is
going to have to start breaking
up.
It's going to have to start
attacking each other.
I mean, they-they can't all go
to the final spot.
I mean, it's just not going to
happen.
>> Ooh!
>> I thought were going to do a
back flip.
>> Wow.
>> That was beautiful, Danni.
>> Thank you, thank you.
I'm seeing stars.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
Go ahead and take a spot on the
bench.
>> (laughs)
>> JEFF: Welcome to the Survivor
auction.
You each have $500 US.
Sharing of money is allowed, but
only the two people who pool
their money can share in the
item.
The auction will end without
warning.
Everyone here is not guaranteed
an item.
If you see something you like,
you should bid on it.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: Get to the first item.
A plate of beef jerky.
>> Oh.
>> JEFF: A little protein.
>> Twenty.
>> JEFF: Danni's on the board
for 20.
Steph, not even interested.
Nobody else wants this?
Going once.
Going twice.
Sold to Danni for 20 bucks.
Pretty good bargain at 20 bucks,
right?
>> Right.
>> JEFF: Let me tempt you with
this.
>> Oh, no.
>> JEFF: You can keep your beef
jerky for 20 bucks or you can
trade it for what's covered.
>> I'm going with the beef
jerky.
>> JEFF: Come on up.
>> 20 bucks.
>> JEFF: You know what you have.
Let's see what you didn't take.
Uncooked corn.
>> Whoo!
>> (laughing): Oh!
>> JEFF: Something nobody wants.
Ready for the next item?
Three chocolate chip cookies.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God.
>> JEFF: Tall glass of milk.
>> Twenty.
>> JEFF: Lydia says 20.
>> I'll go 40.
>> JEFF: Cindy in on that at 40.
$40 to Cindy.
Anybody else want it?
Going once.
Going twice.
Sold to Cindy for 40 bucks.
>> Yay!
Cookies, cookies.
>> JEFF: Take a bite of one of
those.
Dipping right in.
>> Got big chunks of chocolate.
That makes me happy.
>> Let me see.
Oh, those are nice cookies.
>> JEFF: Next item is not a food
item.
Individual mosquito net.
>> (gasps)
>> Twenty.
>> Forty.
>> Sixty.
>> I'll split it with you for
80.
>> Can we split it 80?
>> JEFF: Rafe and Danni at 80.
>> Hundred.
>> JEFF: Lydia, 100 bucks for
the mosquito net.
>> Hundred twenty.
>> JEFF: Rafe and Danni going
120.
>> One forty.
>> JEFF: 140 to Lydia.
Going once, going twice.
Sold to Lydia.
>> I need it.
>> JEFF: You need it?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: All right.
It's yours.
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: You don't need to share
it.
Boy, you do have a lot of bites
on that back.
Wow!
>> You haven't seen nothing yet.
>> JEFF: Got it on the booty,
too?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Next item.
Covered.
Going to stay covered.
>> Oh.
>> JEFF: Could be the steal of
the day.
>> Twenty.
>> JEFF: Lydia, 20.
>> Forty.
>> JEFF: Danni to 40.
>> Sixty.
>> A hundred.
>> 120, Judd and I.
>> JEFF: 120, Judd and Steph.
>> One forty.
>> JEFF: People got an inkling
this is something good.
>> 160, Jeff.
>> JEFF: 160 to Steph and Judd.
>> Going once.
Going twice.
>> Okay, let's do it.
180.
>> Okay, 180.
>> JEFF: Rafe and Danni, 180.
Too rich for Steph and Judd?
>> Yep.
>> JEFF: Danni and Rafe, sold
for 180.
Come on up.
$180 for this.
>> (screaming)
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God!
>> JEFF: Got a Philly steak
sandwich, fries, ketchup.
>> Take a big old bite of that.
>> Oh, my God, it's humongous.
>> JEFF: Take it back.
>> Watch Cindy's head.
>> JEFF: Judd, how does that
look?
>> Whew!
Paradise.
>> JEFF: Ready for the next
item?
Something a little different.
Inside this envelope is a huge
advantage at the next immunity
challenge.
Whether or not it is enough to
make sure you win depends on how
you use it, but if you think you
are in trouble, this is worth
bidding on.
>> Twenty.
>> Forty.
>> Sixty.
>> Eighty.
>> JEFF: Danni at 80 first.
>> Hundred.
>> Hundred twenty.
>> One forty.
>> JEFF: Steph, 140.
Danni, 160.
>> One eighty.
>> Two hundred.
>> JEFF: 200 to Danni.
Anybody else in this?
Going once.
Going twice.
Sold for 200 to Danni.
Here's the deal, Danni.
This has a wax seal on it.
It needs to remain sealed.
We'll deal with it when you get
to the next challenge.
>> Okay.
Whoo-hoo!
>> JEFF: Next item up for bids
coming right around the corner.
>> (screaming)
>> (laughing)
>> JEFF: Cindy, there's your
twin sister, Mindy.
Rafe, your mom, Lonnie.
Danni, your brother, Drew.
Judd, your wife, Kristin.
Lydia, there's your brother,
Joseph.
And Steph, your boyfriend,
Michael.
Rafe, a little odd to see your
mom out here?
>> This is so random.
I can't believe she's standing
in front of my eyes.
>> JEFF: Lydia, this is first
time in two years you've seen
Joseph.
How's he look?
>> Good.
Real good.
>> JEFF: How's Lydia look?
>> Strong.
>> JEFF: Okay, you are bidding
on an overnight stay.
Your loved one will come back to
camp with you.
They'll spend the night.
They'll see how you've been
living for the last month.
Only two people can share money,
but only one person gets their
loved one, so somebody would be
helping somebody else out.
>> Bidding starts at 40 bucks.
>> Forty.
>> JEFF: Steph, 40.
>> Eighty.
>> JEFF: Judd at 80.
>> Hundred.
>> JEFF: Lydia with 100.
>> Hundred and thirty.
>> JEFF: 130.
>> Hundred and forty.
>> JEFF: Cindy, 140.
>> Three hundred.
>> JEFF: Rafe goes to 300.
It's gonna get down to sharing
of money now.
>> How much do you have?
>> I got 200.
>> JEFF: Steph asking Lydia for
a favor.
>> Will you give me 200?
>> JEFF: Cindy, you're giving
him everything you have?
>> I was already out.
I already didn't have enough.
>> JEFF: Steph takes all of
Lydia's money.
She's counting it up.
Judd has taken all of Cindy's
money.
>> 40, 60, 80...
>> JEFF: Who's getting a visit
with their loved one?
>> 20, 40, 50...
There is 750.
>> JEFF: Steph has $750
combining her money with Lydia.
>> 20, 40, 60, 80, 700.
20, 40, 60, 80, 800.
40, 70, 880.
>> JEFF: Eight eighty.
Steph has done everything she
can.
>> Judd has bought his loved
one for 880 bucks.
>> Kristin, go give him some
love.
(applause)
>> JEFF: You're going with him,
Kristin, like it or not.
Judd, in addition to having
Kristin spend the night, you
have purchased the right to
invite two other loved ones to
camp with you as well.
>> Judd, please...
>> Oh, yes!
>> JEFF: While you and the loved
ones will all go back to your
camp, the three survivors who
you do not pick will go back to
the old Yaxha camp and spend the
night alone.
They will not get anything, not
so much as a hug.
So you're going to make two
people really happy and three
people really unhappy.
>> I mean, Cindy, of course.
If it wasn't for her, my wife
wouldn't be here.
>> JEFF: Mindy, you are going to
get the Survivor experience.
(applause)
>> She's still strong.
>> JEFF: All right, Judd.
Now you got a big choice left.
Rafe, crying at seeing his mom.
Stephanie tried to outbid to you
to see her boyfriend.
Lydia hasn't seen her brother in
two years.
>> I'm going to take my Jersey
girl with me.
>> JEFF: Michael, give her a
hug.
>> (laughing)
>> (applause)
>> JEFF: Steph, take Michael
back over to the bench.
>> This is Judd.
(laughing)
>> JEFF: Got three very happy
survivors and three survivors
who are going to have a rough
night alone.
Say your good-byes, guys.
>> Take care.
Keep up the good work, all
right?
>> Bye, Joe.
>> Bye.
Be tough.
>> (sobbing)
>> (mumbles)
>> Love you.
>> JEFF: All right, Lydia,
Danni, Rafe, head on out.
>> Bye, guys.
>> JEFF: All right, guys.
Take them back to camp.
>> Welcome home, folks.
Michael, Kristy and Mindy, this
is what we call home for 31
days, man.
And that's how we get our water,
our wood and everything.
This is why Uncle Chub lost 40
pounds.
This is where we live for 31
days.
This is what we call home, man.
This is what we've been living
in, so welcome to beautiful
Guatemala.
>> Thank you.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Finally.
>> Judd, you learned how to make
fire?
>> I'm, like, the Iron Man.
>> Get out!
No way!
>> My wife was pretty shocked,
man, at my camping skills.
She was digging it.
She thought it was pretty hot.
She thought I was a sexy camper.
This is how we get our water,
'cause you're always dehydrated
here.
This is lake water that we got
to boil.
Just drink it right out.
>> Really?
Can I have a little?
He knows what he's doing.
I never thought he'd know what
to do.
I'm shocked, 'cause he seems
like he's doing it all.
I'm very proud of him.
I'm impressed.
>> Usually, we take our palm
fronds and we spread them out
all over here.
People who sleep by the fire.
And I sleep right here.
>> I'm excited to be here,
because this is what I grew up
doing.
Playing wilderness people was
our favorite thing to play.
It's, like, our greatest
adventure yet.
>> The first two days was an
11.
5-mile hike.
We had to stop and just sleep in
the jungle somewhere.
Through thick jungle.
It was horrible.
We thought we were going to die.
Oh, my God.
To have Mike here-- it's a dream
come true.
I owe Judd big time, 'cause this
is the second time he's given me
a sweet reward and shared a
sweet reward with me.
>> This is all coming down to
the wire here, but we-we've got
got a tight alliance here.
It's me, Steph, Cindy and Rafe
in an alliance right now that's
tight as can be.
Steph, I hope, goes my way.
That takes me to the final two,
if all goes well.
>> It's been awhile since we've
been here, Rafe.
>> No kidding.
>> Wow, this is our...
>> It's been, like, 20 days...
>> Day one camp.
>> We came back to the old Yaxha
camp today after the reward
challenge, and it was like a
homecoming of sorts, getting to
the camp and seeing that old
lean-to.
How long are we going to be
here?
But also, like, a fight for
survival.
I think we should be really
careful about, you know, what's
happening, and I trust you a
lot.
>> It's hard to trust anybody.
That's why Gary told me I could
trust you.
He's like, "Just, you know,
stick with Rafe."
>> And that's same thing he told
me.
Judd's the only one that I feel
is, like, ready to break.
>> Yeah, he's...
Yeah.
>> You know?
>> He's a threat.
He's definitely a threat.
The only person I really feel
like I can trust now is Rafe.
I think he knows that I'm
important to have around for
him because that alliance is
going to start wanting to vote
somebody out, and they have to
see Rafe as threat.
Um, so he needs another buddy.
I'm sure Judd or Cindy is going
to approach me, 'cause they're
going to have to number-wise.
>> Right.
>> If he talks to me or talks to
Lydia, tries to vote against
you, we'll just let you know.
>> Well, he's in control kind
of, but also in a really tenuous
position because you and me are
way closer than him and me.
And, like, we just need to catch
Judd in some kind of lie.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> So that we can show Steph
that that's...
'Cause right now, she really,
really trusts him.
I know that Judd is threatened
by me.
I know that Judd might want to
get me out before he says he
does, so I have to make back-up
plans so that if he tries, then
I'll be safe.
You can't trust a person like
Judd, but you can trust that you
can't trust him.
>> So, so, Cindy, we-we should
be all right for...
still with
our final four.
The reason I'm saying that is
because Danni does have that
clue.
Okay, good, take that clue,
fine, you know what I mean?
Go ahead.
>> She's not usually a front-
runner.
>> No, she's not a threat at
all, so that's good for us.
>> Mentally or physically, she's
not usually a front-runner.
One thing she's good at is
shooting basketballs.
>> That's it, so we have an edge
on her.
>> She must have something if
she made it this far.
>> If she wins, that's-that's
okay.
I mean, it's not the end of our
world right here.
If she wins it, that's fine.
Then we get rid of Lydia.
God, I'm so glad this worked out
this way.
>> They told me the mother lode.
I just get my whole bunch, then
I'm good for the night.
That's all we do.
We make two wood runs a day.
That's it.
(mosquitoes buzzing)
>> (grunting)
>> It's a lot more barren than I
had expected, that's for sure.
They have nothing, and it's so
much work.
Everything they do is just such
a chore, really.
>> This is a real deal, and most
people would not survive out
here in a, you know, a day.
It's crazy.
>> Hmm.
>> We're back.
>> Hey.
>> Hi, guys.
>> Hey!
>> Hey, you!
Still there.
>> Hi.
>> We just started making corn.
>> What do you say there, Mr.
Rafe-inator?
>> We just came back and walked
in, and we didn't think that the
family members would still be
here, but they are.
Um, and so it's been kind of
nice.
We got to meet them all, talk to
them, see that they're not
loving camp life at all.
>> So, what'd you think about
this experience?
>> I've never camped ever before
in my life.
I don't know how you do it.
>> It felt great having my wife
here at camp.
I haven't been eating, so I feel
like she actually made me full
just by looking at her.
It's like eating 25 White Castle
cheeseburgers, man.
(all saying good-byes)
>> I'll see you soon.
>> Nice meeting you.
Good luck.
Bye.
>> Nice meeting you.
>> We all walked down here to
the boat dock and had to say
good-bye to our loved ones.
And it was hard, but I'm glad
she was here to see it.
She wished me lots of luck and
she knows I can do it, man.
I'm going to do it.
>> You've made it through the
hard part.
>> I know.
>> I love you so much.
I've missed Judd so much.
The longest I've never spoke to
him was, like, 24 hours.
And, um...
I just can't wait for
him to come home.
>> I just thought it was really
incredible that my sister got to
be here.
It's just going to make it even
more of a memorable experience
forever.
>> Bye.
>> Bye, you guys.
>> Bye, you guys!
>> It was bittersweet, but it
was more sweet than anything
else.
I hate good-byes.
So I can't wait to say hello.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> Judd was talking about how
it's important to get rid of the
strongest, um, you know,
survivors that are left.
And Rafe has the, uh...
talked
to me the day before and said,
you know, "If Judd says anything
about voting me off, I think we
can get Stephenie's vote against
Judd."
And I know Lydia and I are
desperate.
We'll, you know, stick with him.
>> Judd, you know what?
Maybe it's time we make a deal.
>> You know what?
I don't have a problem with
that.
>> It's funny.
The longer you stick around, the
more problems you can cause.
You know, more doors will open,
so it seems like I have a little
bit of a crack.
(laughs)
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
First things first.
Rafe, give up immunity.
You've had this for awhile.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
All right, let's get to today's
challenge.
It is for immunity.
It requires smarts.
It's a bit of a human chess
game.
Here is how it works.
One at a time, you're each going
to make a move on our multi-
level board by flipping a tile
to its red side and stepping on
it.
You can move forward.
You can move backward.
You can move side to side.
You cannot move diagonally.
Once you stepped off the red
tile, no one can step onto it
again.
In addition, the top platform is
a spinning platform, so if at
any time, you want to
strategically relocate yourself
to somewhere else on the board,
spin yourself to a new spot.
As you all move around the
board, there will be fewer and
fewer white tiles to flip over.
At some point, you'll run out of
tiles to step onto.
When that happens, you're out of
the game.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, guarantees themselves
a spot in the final five.
Danni, at the auction, you
purchased an advantage...
>> Yep.
>> JEFF: ...
to today's immunity
challenge.
You still have the envelope?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: Okay, let me see it.
Still sealed.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> JEFF: Good, don't open it
yet.
>> I'm a good girl.
>> JEFF: Take a spot on the
board, and we'll get started.
All right, we've drawn for spots
on the board.
Danni, time to open your
immunity advantage.
>> See what it is.
>> JEFF: Read it out loud.
>> Switch positions with
any player.
>> JEFF: So, what that means is,
at any time in this game you can
trade spots with any player one
time.
If you understand how to play
this game, that is a huge
advantage.
If you don't, it might just
extend your life a little
longer.
>> Let's find out.
Everybody make your first
move.
Everybody's on the board.
Danni, you're up.
Cindy.
Danni goes sideways.
Cindy goes forward.
Judd.
Rafe.
Steph.
Lydia.
Danni.
Cindy.
Cindy continues to move
forward.
Judd.
Rafe.
Stephenie.
Anxious to go.
Lydia.
Everybody with a slightly
different game plan.
Cindy, going up to the
spinning platform.
Going to spin herself into a
new spot.
Lydia, which tile is she
going to move?
Cindy, surrounded by a sea of
red.
No more tiles to flip over.
Cindy can't move.
She's first one out of the game.
Take a spot on the bench.
Steph is up.
Steph's carved out a nice
piece of real estate.
Danni, your move.
>> Can I switch?
>> JEFF: You can switch any time
you want.
Immunity and a spot in the final
five is riding on this
challenge.
>> I want to switch with Steph.
>> JEFF: Danni uses her immunity
advantage.
Steph doesn't like it.
Danni, Steph, switch
positions.
Only time will tell if it was
the right move.
Lydia.
Takes her last move.
>> Last move.
>> JEFF: Step on it then take a
spot on the bench next to Cindy.
Lydia, second person out of
the game.
We're down to four.
Danni, Judd, Rafe on one side
of the board.
Steph alone on the other.
Judd, your move.
Rafe's turn.
Starting to get interesting.
Danni.
Steph.
Judd.
Rafe.
Rafe and Danni closing in on
the same tiles.
Danni.
Danni makes her move, and in
doing so, ends the game for
Rafe, who has nowhere left to
move.
>> Good job, Rafe.
>> JEFF: Rafe joins Lydia and
Cindy on the bench.
We are down to three.
Steph.
Judd.
Judd makes his last move.
>> I've got one more.
>> JEFF: Judd, you cannot move
diagonally.
Nowhere left to go.
You're out of the game.
We're down to two.
Danni and Steph.
Danni made Steph switch
positions with her.
Steph, only so many tiles
left to work with.
Just play it out now.
Danni.
With that, Steph has only one
move left to make.
Steph is out.
Danni wins immunity.
Well played.
Well spent.
>> Well spent.
>> JEFF: Money well spent.
Danni, come on up.
(applause)
A lot of things bid on at
that auction.
Nothing more valuable than
this right now.
>> I love this thing.
>> JEFF: Well played.
You are safe tonight at
Tribal Council.
Steph, Judd, Cindy, Lydia,
Rafe, after 33 days, one of you
is going home tonight.
See you at Tribal Council.
Head on back to camp.
>> Good job.
>> Good job, Danni.
>> Thank you.
>> I don't know about you...
>> I thought I'd be going next
for sure.
That was like the biggest
immunity I could ever win.
There's lot of things going on
right now.
So something may work out even
more so in my favor tonight.
>> Where did Judd go?
>> I'd like to believe Judd.
I believe Judd for the most part
but already made clear that he's
playing this game and do
anything to win.
He's already been caught in
quite a few lies.
And Danni really hasn't lied at
all.
>> Whoa.
>> Said a million times he's
like, "I'm here to win.
I'll do whatever it takes."
>> We have to be...
>> We've been trying to be
honest.
>> For the most part.
>> Like I don't know...
>> We were saying if he goes
tonight we'll want Lydia to go
next then we'll go to the four.
>> Yeah.
>> With Cindy.
>> I mean, what do you think?
What if Cindy...
if we vote for
Judd, they all vote for us.
>> I think Lydia will vote for
us.
>> She said she would vote for
Judd.
>> I think she would.
>> You do?
And what, do we tell Cindy?
>> What do you think?
>> My heart tells me get rid of
Lydia because Judd and I have
been really close.
>> At the same time, if someone
is going to slit your throat
because they like your company,
hell, no, they got to go.
>> I love Judd, though.
I do.
I told his wife that we were
sticking together.
I feel horrible.
But if he's likely to turn, I
can't...
You know, I never...
>> I basically told Stephenie
what was going on now.
And now she's kinda thinking
maybe we might vote Judd out
tonight.
So hopefully my plan worked to
rat Judd out.
>> Absolutely.
>> It's weird how the original
plan was to take Danni out.
She won immunity on the day that
she needed it, you know what I'm
saying?
I'm here if you want to use my
vote.
If not.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Arrivederci.
Sayonara.
Good-bye.
>> Nobody is safe here tonight.
If you think you're safe in this
game, you're crazy.
>> Yeah.
>> You're absolutely berserk.
>> If anybody needs me for their
vote, I'm here for them.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I'm not about to give up.
I'm not about to quit.
>> We have alliance to me,
Cindy, Stephenie and Rafe.
And we had agreed if Danni won
immunity it's going to be Lydia.
>> Do you know if she's lied?
>> She's working, man.
I said it could be me, it could
be you.
>> It could be Rafe.
>> That's what I said.
I said it could be anybody here.
>> That's funny.
>> No, it's not.
But you got to say something.
I mean, you can't just sit
there.
You know what I mean?
Jellybean?
>> I know what you mean,
jellybean.
>> Yeah, I'll miss Lydia around
camp.
I'll miss her singing and
dancing, all that.
But one other person goes I move
up.
No hard feelings.
So, you know, pretty glad
somebody's going home right now.
As long as it ain't me, man,
I'll always have a smile on my
face.
>> JEFF: We now bring in the
members of our jury.
Bobby Jon, Jamie, and Gary voted
out last Tribal Council.
So let's talk about the loved
ones.
Steph, you and Michael have been
going out seven years?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: It had to be just
wonderful to have him out there
and experience that with you.
>> Yeah, it was really special
and really awesome because now
he can really understand what
we've all been going through,
and it was just like, "This
sucks."
He's like, "You guys are tough."
>> JEFF: Let's talk about the
immunity challenge.
Danni, you are smiling from ear
to ear right now.
>> Oh, my, gosh.
When it came up in the auction
to get the advantage, there was
no way I was going to let that
pass.
And fortunately it worked out.
And like I started to cry.
I've cried twice over spaghetti
and over immunity.
So I was very, very happy and
needed it.
>> JEFF: Cindy, take me through
that process emotionally of how
it becomes more difficult to
vote tonight.
>> You have to consider the
person you're voting out and how
their alliance is going to
affect your alliance with
whoever is left.
Also the person that's going
home is going to have some say
if you end up in the final two
and whether or not you win.
So you got 20 things going
through your head that you have
to consider.
>> JEFF: Rafe, have you started
to consider how it's going to be
different after tonight's Tribal
Council when you are now down to
odd number, five.
>> It's like, you don't know
exactly who to trust, but you
have to like kind of believe
that you have the right gut
feeling about who you can trust
around here.
Because that's the only thing
that's going to get to you the
end of the game at this point.
With this few people left you
have to have strong trust to get
to the end of the game.
>> JEFF: Steph, how important is
it to you how you vote somebody
out of this game?
>> For me it's important to vote
somebody out and know that
you're making the right choice
and be able to, if you make it
to the final two, to explain
yourself.
Explain your reasoning behind
it.
And it's hard.
Because you let your emotions
get to you.
We are all fighting for a
million bucks, but we're
like family.
We really are.
>> JEFF: Judd, somebody in this
family will be going tonight.
>> Well, I tell what you, to be
honest with you, no matter what
they all say, everybody wants
somebody to go home.
I mean, they're sitting here
making believe like, oh, man,
going to stink.
That's not the case, man.
Everybody wants somebody to go
home.
That's the bottom line.
That's what we're here for.
Only way you move on is somebody
goes home.
No hard feelings, but deal with
it.
That's basically the way I look
at it.
If somebody goes home, that's
better for me.
You just got to trust and love
the ones you're with right now.
>> JEFF: Danni, you paid a lot
of money to get that immunity
around your neck.
I can't imagine you're giving it
up.
>> No, I think I'm going to keep
it.
>> JEFF: Danni is the only one
you cannot vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
Time to vote.
Rafe, you're up.
>> You're always saying we're a
bunch of squirrels trying to get
a nut.
Well, sorry, I had to write your
name down, but I had to do what
I had to do today.
>> Hey, Lydia, you sang and you
danced your way right out of
the jungle.
Adios.
>> JEFF: I'll tally the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Judd.
Lydia.
One vote Lydia.
Two votes Lydia, one vote Judd.
Judd.
Two votes Judd, two votes Lydia.
That's three votes Judd,
two votes Lydia.
One vote left.
13th person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala: Judd.
>> Thanks, guys.
Hope you guys all get bit by a
freakin' crocodile.
Scumbags.
>> JEFF: Judd, the Tribe has
spoken.
Time to go.
>> JEFF: After tonight's vote
one thing should be very clear:
you can no longer rely on what
used to be because this game
just took a change in a very big
way.
Grab your torches.
Go back to camp.
Good night.
>> ANNOUNCER: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
>> I see a little pattern there,
and it makes me uncomfortable.
>> JEFF: Cindy is consoled after
Tribal Council.
>> He's not privileged of the
information.
>> Really?
>> JEFF: The strategy deepens.
>> That's tough decision.
>> JEFF: And the tribe is
shocked with an awful dilemma.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I'm really pissed off.
I mean, I feel I was pissed on,
pissed off, lied to, betrayed.
It doesn't feel good being
blind-sided and it sucks being
lied to, man, because one thing
I didn't do was lie to anybody,
man.
Hey, get rid of the biggest
target, and that's what they
did, man.
So, I really believe that you
are a bunch of scumbags, and I
can't wait till the final two,
man. I'll have a lot more to