>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, Yaxha celebrated
their diversity.
>> We got the gay guy, a police
officer, magician's assistant,
and we got a landscaper.
>> I told them I was a
landscaper, not a quarterback.
Nobody's asked me what I did 15
years ago.
So I guess I don't have to tell
them.
>> PROBST: At Nakum, right
before the challenge, things
were not looking good for Blake.
>> Yeah, it's bad, man.
>> He's struggling to
get breaths, and something's not
right.
>> PROBST: At the challenge, the
tribes competed for fishing
supplies.
Survivors ready?
Go!
The race was close, but in the
end, Blake made a comeback and
led Nakum to victory.
Nakum wins reward!
Nakum put their new fishing gear
to good use.
>> I got one. I got one.
>> Yes! Yes!
>> Breakfast.
>> PROBST: At Yaxha, the food
situation was grim.
>> You want to eat ants?
>> I'm not gonna be eating ants.
>> PROBST: But with minimal
resources, Lydia managed to
provide.
>> Did you have any luck down
there?
>> Ten little minnows.
>> That's a minnow each.
>> You know what they
say, the way to a man's heart is
through their stomachs.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, both tribes duked it
out in a difficult tug-of-war
mud bath.
When the challenge moved to
individual face-offs, Danni gave
Yaxha a clue to Gary's true
identity.
>> He's a quarterback.
You're like a linebacker.
Come on.
>> PROBST: Judd went on to
dominate the challenge and
pulled Nakum to victory.
Judd makes a big pull!
This challenge is over!
Nakum wins immunity!
With Tribal Council looming,
Brian questioned Gary about his
past.
>> Gary, were you a former NFL
quarterback?
>> Me?
>> Yeah.
>> No.
I'm just going to deny
I played in the NFL because I
think I would be voted off
immediately.
>> PROBST: Eventually it was
Lydia and Morgan on the chopping
block.
>> Longevity-wise, who do you
think will be better?
>> Lydia is limited in the
challenges.
But Morgan doesn't do very much
in camp.
>> PROBST: Brian scrambled to
save Lydia.
>> I told her, I said
"Lydia, it's not looking good
for you," because she needs to
know.
>> PROBST: So Lydia made a plea
to Gary.
>> I'm not ready to go, Gary.
>> PROBST: The plea worked.
At Tribal Council Lydia was
spared and Morgan got a big
surprise when she was voted out
of Yaxha.
Morgan, the tribe has spoken.
16 are left-- who will be voted
out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Last night was our first
Tribal Council, and Morgan
got voted out, but I really
believe that my head was on the
chopping block.
I'm a hard worker.
You know, I don't deserve to go.
The person that I would have
chose would have been Brianna.
Because she's kind of on the
weak side, and we need a strong
tribe.
We have to start winning.
>> Oh, yeah.
I've been hearing that
thunder for a little bit now.
>> I don't get along with Lydia.
We don't fight.
I'm cordial with her, but she's
just not my cup of tea.
>> Day seven.
>> Guys, no more Tribal Council,
okay?
That sucks.
>> I actually had no idea how it
was gonna turn out.
I was just hoping.
>> It was a last-minute pull
that I thought worked out good.
>> Last night was so great.
I was so happy with the outcome.
That was 100% me.
I engineered Morgan's ouster.
But if Lydia had to go next, I
wouldn't throw a big fit about
it.
'Cause I will do whatever I need
to do to make sure it's going my
way.
( loud screeching )
>> I believe it's day seven.
In seven days, I probably slept
a couple of hours.
They got this damn monkey up
here that's just driving me out
of my mind.
( screeching continues )
I mean, I don't know how anybody
could sleep through that, if
they're saying they're sleeping
through that.
>> No, they are loud.
( screeching continues )
>> How can I complain about
being woken up by howler monkeys
in Guatemala?
People pay money to do that.
They've got all this loose skin
in their throat, and it gets all
big like a bowling ball, and
they let the air out and it
makes that crazy noise.
>> It's absolutely miserable.
It just goes on and on.
And then we've got like a
zookeeper here, Cindy.
She's like, almost like a Dr.
Dolittle.
The monkey's lost and he's
looking for the brother that's
all the way across the other
side of the jungle.
And I'm like, dude...
That is the most annoyingest
noise I've ever heard in my
entire life.
It just, it really, it just
drives you crazy, man.
It makes you nuts.
( screeching continues )
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Nakum, getting your first look
at the new Yaxha tribe.
Morgan voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
All right, let's get to today's
challenge.
Here in Guatemala, you guys are
surrounded by ruins that are in
various stages of excavation by
archaeologists who are searching
for more clues into the Maya
culture.
That plays into today's
challenge.
You're going to build an
archaeologist's tent.
You will be blindfolded and tied
together in groups.
One person on each tribe will be
your set of eyes.
They will guide you.
Scattered amongst these ruins
will be nine bundles of items.
Once you've found all nine
bundles, take off your
blindfolds, start putting the
tent together.
Poles to build the frame, a tarp
for the top, and rope to keep it
all together.
First tribe to complete it
correctly wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Comfort.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Nice.
>> PROBST: Pillows, a lantern
and fuel, tarp, rope, blankets.
All right, I need callers.
Nakum?
>> I'm going to be the caller,
Jeff.
>> PROBST: Brooke will be the
caller. Yaxha?
Gary will be the set of eyes.
We'll get you blindfolded and
we'll get started.
Pick a spot.
Here we go, guys.
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
>> Stephenie, straight
ahead 20 steps.
>> Go a little to your left,
Bobby Jon.
>> Five more steps, Amy.
Five more steps, Steph,
and then lean down and grab.
Keep walking till you hit it.
You got it, you got it.
Right there!
Lean forward, Amy!
Bring it home.
>> Blake, stop, you got a pole.
Pick that up, carry it to the
mat.
Stop, Margaret.
>> Ow, ow, ow!
>> Watch your head, Danni.
>> Come on!
I'm caught up.
>> Sorry about that, Danni.
>> This way, this way!
Keep coming to me.
Drop it!
>> Okay, drop it.
>> Okay, right two more steps,
set it down.
>> PROBST: Yaxha with their
first two items.
>> Bobby Jon, watch out for the
table on your left.
>> Ow! God!
>> Okay, set it down, set it
down.
Bobby Jon, set yours down.
>> PROBST: Nakum drops off their
first three items.
>> Stop, Jamie.
Left five steps, 90 degrees.
>> Four, five.
I got a pole.
>> Margaret, straight towards
me, straight ahead.
>> PROBST: Margaret took one in
the shoulder.
Nakum with four, Yaxha with
their third.
>> Okay, Steph.
>> Margaret and Bobby Jon, drop
it.
>> PROBST: Nakum with two more--
they're now at six.
>> Keep coming in.
Drop it right there.
Left more, left more, drop it!
>> PROBST: Yaxha at five.
>> Margaret, stop.
You guys go to your left.
Go to your left.
Wait, go to your right more,
sorry.
Blake, drop your stuff.
>> PROBST: Nakum at seven.
>> Keep going, keep going,
Steph!
There, you got it.
Bring it back.
>> Go back this way.
Follow me.
>> Please tell me when you're
picking up a pole, and I'll
duck.
>> Bobby Jon, bend down.
You got it.
>> Gary, am I going the right
way?
>> This way, this way!
Keep coming to me.
>> Gary, am I close?
Can I throw it? Gar?
>> PROBST: That's six for Yaxha.
>> All right, drop your stuff.
>> PROBST: Nakum at eight.
>> Keep doing what you're doing.
Drop it.
>> PROBST: Yaxha at seven,
coming back with their eighth
item.
>> Drop it right now, Amy.
>> PROBST: We're tied,
eight-eight.
It's a race for the last item.
>> Stop, Steph!
Right 90 degrees.
Five steps.
>> Cindy, left.
Okay, now your right a little.
Follow them.
>> Keep going! No.
To the right. Yeah!
Yes! Straight back to me.
Straight ahead, straight ahead,
straight ahead, drop it.
>> PROBST: Yaxha has their ninth
item.
Take off your blindfolds.
Start assembling.
>> Girls untie, boys build.
Girls untie, boys build.
>> Put the poles in.
>> PROBST: Yaxha with a big
advantage right now.
>> Behind you, Margaret, to your
left.
>> PROBST: Nakum, still working.
Got to hustle.
>> Margaret, this way, towards
your left!
>> Anything in between us?
>> No, but walk fast.
>> This has holes in it, Gary.
>> PROBST: Yaxha, putting their
frame together.
Nakum coming back with their
last item.
>> Stop, drop it.
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfolds!
Nakum has all nine items, they
start assembling.
Yaxha with a big lead.
>> Uh, that's not right.
>> PROBST: This is going to come
down to how quickly and how
efficiently the two tribes work
together.
>> Look at the top.
The top has all the holes.
>> Flip it over, 'cause it says
Yaxha on the other side.
>> Put this in somewhere, guys.
>> It's got to go underneath.
Underneath.
>> What the hell?
>> PROBST: A lot of confusion at
Yaxha.
>> Go.
Raise it, raise it, raise it.
Put it down.
>> PROBST: Nakum has a plan.
Making up a lot of ground.
>> That one, that one.
That's the big one that goes
here.
>> It has to go over all the top
holes.
>> Through the tall ones in
middle.
>> PROBST: Yaxha cannot figure
out their frame.
>> Okay, line 'em up, line 'em
up.
Let's go, let's go!
>> PROBST: Nakum working well
together.
We are dead even.
>> Let's go, let's go.
Come on, grab this side.
>> PROBST: Both tribes moving on
to their tarps.
You're going to have to use
those ropes to keep them
together.
>> Somebody get on the ropes!
Ropes go on the other side
poles!
>> PROBST: Very close, very
close.
>> Right there.
Go, go, go, go, go, hurry,
hurry!
>> PROBST: When you think you
have it right, get on your mat.
>> Drop that side on.
Drop that side.
>> PROBST: Wrong ropes.
>> This one's not reaching.
>> PROBST: Both tribes trying to
figure out which ropes are the
right ropes.
It's coming down to the wire.
>> It's this one!
Give me that one!
>> Gary, this is longer.
This is longer, Gary.
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
>> Mat, mat, mat, mat, mat, mat.
Hurry!
>> PROBST: Nakum wins reward.
( cheering )
Yaxha, good effort, good
calling.
You fell apart when it came to
putting the tent together.
I got nothing for you.
Head on back to camp.
Nakum, good job, kept it
together, didn't panic, caught
up, won a nice reward.
Get your stuff.
Head on back to camp.
>> The reward challenge was so
easy.
I mean, we were like totally in
the lead, and then we all start
building like lunatics, and it
was just, like, a big...
cluster mess.
I did not even want that reward.
I just wanted to win.
>> So close! Gosh!
>> I'm just hoping that it's so
early on in this game that we're
going to pull it out.
I believe that can happen, I
really do.
I've been in worse situations.
( laughs )
>> We can't afford to lose
those.
>> That was the easiest
challenge ever.
>> Yeah, but we lost it.
That's what sucks.
>> I know.
>> It sucks to lose.
You get down for about two
minutes, and then you come back
strong.
You know, I don't feel
fantastic, but I know what I
have to do to make it out here.
>> I've been sleeping in it for
seven days, and I'm loving it!
Does anybody else's clothes look
like that?
Why are you laughing?
Do your clothes look like that?
>> If you boil it, it might
help.
>> This is gonna rot.
I can't believe I'm living like
this.
If you think about it, like, no
soap, we're brushing our teeth
with a tree.
We're going to the bathroom and
using leaves.
One pair of underwear.
This is torture.
>> Yeah, but the worst thing is,
it's only day seven.
It gets, like, a lot worse.
>> Listen, you're in paradise,
look-it.
>> Yeah, paradise, we can't
even swim, we can't even go
swimming and have a water game
because there's crocs in there
that might bite our butts.
>> Hey, you're not working at
the police station.
>> That's a walk in the park
compared to this.
I have no outdoor experience,
absolutely nothing.
But could I hack it out here 39
days?
Absolutely.
I'll never give up.
You'll have to stick needles in
my eyeballs, I'm still not going
to give up.
I don't care how bad it gets,
I will not give up.
>> We did it.
>> We're on a streak.
>> Four to one, baby, four to
one.
>> One game at a time, you know?
>> And just enjoy the moment,
man.
>> Feeling real good.
We won our reward challenge
today, and I'm not too used to
winning, so it felt good to win.
>> Let's all take a breather and
regroup here.
>> Yeah.
>> We deserve a rest.
( groans )
>> We think we want to build a
better shelter, just put the
tarp up, but we got to wait
for the heat to pass.
The heat's definitely taken
its toll on getting work done.
>> This is hotter than Texas.
>> Yeah, it is hotter than
Texas.
>> It's Arizona with the
humidity.
>> Who cares, man?
Let's just get in the water,
dude.
Y'all ready? You ready?
>> I'm ready to dive right in.
>> This is definitely one of the
toughest things I've ever done
in my entire life.
I mean, the heat is beating the
crap out of us, and then can't
really jump in the water to cool
off because of the alligators.
>> You shoving off?
>> Yeah, man, we're going out.
>> We're not going out far,
right?
>> The crocs are around here.
We got to go out a little bit
further.
>> They're all over.
>> It's just so hot out, and,
God, that water is just so
tempting.
>> Who's not going?
>> That's all right.
>> I'm going to get off, too.
I'm not getting in there.
I've worked with alligators.
They behave like crocs do,
and I know they're out there,
even though we can't see them.
There's probably hundreds in
this lake, if not more.
>> We're touching or no?
Uh, yeah, we're touching a
little bit.
>> Everybody watches each
other's backs for the
crocodiles, we'll be all right,
man.
>> Yeah, just look, man.
>> Eventually, you just say
screw it, man, I'll just jump
in, chance it.
Live on the edge a little bit,
you know?
>> They think they're safe
'cause they're in the deep part.
But alligators go deeper when it
gets hot.
They have to regulate their own
body temperature so they're
deeper right now.
They don't care.
They're taking the risk.
They can do what they want.
>> I have to get up.
>> Yeah, baby, go ahead.
>> The brave may not live long,
but the cautious don't live at
all.
And I've never felt more alive
in my entire life.
( laughs )
>> I'm pulling my workload
around camp, because I'm mostly
worried about what my tribe sees
me as.
I want to be considered an asset
on this tribe.
You have to be a provider, and I
believe I am.
Guys, come get it while it's hot
'cause it might stick.
>> Dinner's the same old corn
mush.
It's similar to oatmeal, but not
as good.
Sort of crunchy, like a crunchy,
softish...
stuck-in-your-teeth kind of
meal, I guess you could say.
>> I'm already getting sick of
this smell.
>> Come on, dude, I can't eat
this corn.
>> Mmm!
Everybody, mmm!
>> We have been eating the
same taste every meal, every
day, and we just need something
else.
Like, even throwing dirt in the
corn almost makes it taste
better because it's something
different, and that's all we're
craving right now.
Like, anything different, we
will eat.
>> Look at that?
>> What is that?
>> They said it's termites.
>> That's disgusting.
>> Ew, stop it.
>> Well, I just want to see...
>> Please don't do that.
I'm not going to be your friend
anymore, Rafe.
>> If I eat termites?
>> Yeah.
>> Ew, Rafe!
>> They taste good.
>> Gary, please, stop doing that
or I'm not going to be your
friend, either.
>> Did you like them, Gary?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I think that they're better
than those ants we had.
There's probably more fat in
them.
>> Why don't you cook them up
then?
Don't like eat them alive.
>> Today was a day of
interesting food items.
We started eating termites.
They were good protein, not good
tasting.
>> Good?
>> Protein.
>> What do you guys want to do
with this stuff right now?
>> We could put it over our
existing shelter.
>> We'd get more use out of it
if we tied it up.
>> I agree.
>> There was a little bit of
discussion on how to put the
tarp on.
People always have different
ideas on how things should be
done, but, you know, we all work
as a team.
>> Well, I want to go here, and
then I'm gonna go to that corner
and tie it and go all the way
around it.
>> The guys are trying to
construct a canopy for us to
sleep under, but it's just
interesting how it's taking, you
know, a while.
>> This thing's so heavy, if
rain were to pool on top of it,
it'll collapse.
>> Why don't we all pull a
corner?
>> Um, if you're going to slant
it, you got to decide which way
you want to slant it.
The way this is, if you have it
on there, the canopy may just go
like this, slide along the
string like this.
So knot it so it doesn't slide,
and then do your others.
>> You know, we don't need a
supervisor.
This thing is supposed to be
fun, you know?
>> Ready?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't understand how they
were putting it together 'cause
it was supposed to be a lean.
It looks like we got a, uh,
circus big top for a shelter.
Am I impressed?
( chuckles ): No answer.
>> You have no idea, man.
>> Margaret pretty much hand-
directed building the tent, and,
I don't know, I'm 28 years old.
You just can't tell grown men
what to do all the time.
>> She's playing that mother hen
role.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm not here to take any
orders from her.
I'm like you, man, I'm basically
just here to have fun, man, and
experience it all.
As soon as somebody comes in and
tries to enforce all these
rules, that ain't fun, man.
Margaret just comes in,
"We need this, we need that,"
da, da, da, da, da, da.
Come on, man.
Starting to bark orders this
early is-is not a good thing.
Nobody's going to tell me what
to do.
The only people who tell me what
to do is my boss and my wife,
that's it.
>> We got some tree mail, baby.
>> Exciting, exciting!
>> Let's see what it says.
>> "The ancient Maya
civilization embraced sport.
Considered nobles, the warriors
would adorn themselves in
ceremonial garb and body paint.
When a team of warriors would
lose, the cost would be a human
sacrifice.
You will do the same tonight at
Tribal Council."
>> Oh, you guys, look-it.
>> Oh, fun!
>> Oh, cool!
>> A tree mail came with a big
basket full of feathers, little
bands full of color, lots of
body paint and brushes.
>> I'm going to do football
lines, yeah.
>> You bet.
>> It's fun, because
before I go to Chiefs football
games, we always paint ourselves
up, so it's right up my alley.
Can I put a feather in your
hair?
Nakum is such a strong tribe.
We've won four out of the five
challenges now.
So there's no reason why we
shouldn't go in and win this
one.
>> Guys, we are going to win!
( whooping )
>> We're gonna win, Yaxha!
We got immunity!
We got it, guys.
We need it, we're the underdogs.
Do it for your family, do it for
everyone, do it for each other,
just do it, and win, guys!
>> Guys, for Yaxha.
One, two, three, Yaxha!
>> This immunity challenge is
really important because we
don't want to go to Tribal
Council.
We don't want to lose any more
of my members.
Do I look like I can kick
somebody's butt?
Hopefully, I'll be a star out
there.
Hopefully, I'll do something
that, you know, I won't be the
next one on the chopping block.
I don't want to be that way
again.
>> How do I look?
>> Ah!
I'm scared of you! Whoo!
>> You should be.
We're going to win.
I'm fired up, so I'm trying to
get people up, ready to go,
ready to win.
Right now in terms of people,
we're even, eight to eight.
So if we win tonight, we'll
still be down challenge-wise,
but we'll be up people-wise,
and that's where it's killer.
This is so crucial to keep the
numbers up on our side.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, first things first.
Who has it?
You're tucking it away in there,
Judd.
>> That's right, man.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
back up for grabs.
First of all, glad to see you
took the spirit of today's
challenge to heart and adorned
yourself as warriors.
Definitely plays into the
challenge.
Let's get to today's immunity
It is based on the oldest and
the most popular of Maya games,
called court ball.
Playing on an elevated court,
you will square off three versus
three, attempting to score a
point for your tribe by tossing
this ball through one of your
two hoops.
This is a catch-and-pass game.
That means when you catch it,
you have to pass it.
You cannot run or walk with the
ball.
First tribe to score five points
wins.
Make sense?
At stake?
Well, when the Maya played, the
losing tribe sacrificed a
member.
You will do basically the same
thing tonight-- losers voting
somebody out at Tribal Council.
For each round, the teams of
three will be randomly drawn.
We're going to start with three
men versus three men and mix it
up from there.
Take a spot up on the platform,
and we'll get started.
Judd, Blake, Bobby Jon, taking
on Brian, Rafe and Jamie.
Prepare for battle.
Go!
Jamie first to the ball.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Judd has it.
Blake open.
>> Blake, Blake, Blake!
>> PROBST: Blake tied up from
Jamie.
Judd has it.
Blocked by Jamie.
Bobby Jon has it.
Brian and Rafe have it.
Got to throw it.
Brian has it.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Brian scores for
Yaxha!
Yaxha leads one-zero.
( yelling )
Now we're doing it like the Maya
did.
This round is two men, one
woman.
It's Judd and Blake with
Margaret taking on Rafe and
Jamie with Amy.
Go!
Amy takes one hard on the net.
Blake first to the ball.
Jamie has it, looking for
somebody to throw it to.
Loose ball.
Amy has it!
Amy fighting off Blake!
Trying to find somebody to pass
it to.
Blake steals it.
>> Good shot!
>> PROBST: Blake scores!
We're tied one-one.
>> There you go, Blake!
>> Nice shot, baby.
>> Amy moving a little slowly
after that round.
Next round is all women.
Cindy, Brooke and Danni taking
on Steph, Lydia and Brianna.
Go!
>> Come on, you guys!
>> PROBST: Steph and Danni
mixing it up.
Brianna has it.
>> Get her, get her, get her!
>> PROBST: Danni steals it!
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Long pass to Brooke.
She can't get it.
Steph has it.
Steph and Cindy mixing it up.
Steph needs some help.
>> Brianna, here!
>> You've got to come!
>> PROBST: You got to come to
her.
She can't move.
>> Throw the ball.
>> PROBST: Steph handing off to
Lydia.
Lydia, you got to pass it.
Lydia, no, no, no!
Give it to Brooke.
Nakum's ball.
Lydia traveled.
We're good.
Go.
Brooke passes to Danni.
Danni scores!
Nakum leads two-one.
>> Way to go, baby!
>> PROBST: For this round it is
three men taking on three men
again.
It's Blake, Brandon and Bobby
Jon, taking on Rafe, Gary and
Brian.
Go!
>> Go, Brian!
>> PROBST: Brandon takes one
hard on the net.
Brian fighting off Bobby Jon.
Rafe has it.
Blake steals it.
Passes to Brandon.
Brandon to Bobby Jon.
Can't do it.
Blake does!
Nakum leads three-one.
Temperature update.
114 degrees.
This round is two men, one
woman.
It is Blake, Bobby Jon with
Brooke for Nakum.
For Yaxha, it is Rafe,
Gary and a clearly hurting Amy.
Go!
Bobby Jon and Gary in the
middle.
Bobby Jon has it.
Gary trying to take it from him.
They're still fighting.
Rafe in there.
Rafe has it now.
Got to find somebody to give it
to.
Rafe to Amy.
Amy got to get rid of it.
Back to Gary.
To Rafe.
He's open.
Rafe tosses it through for
Yaxha!
Yaxha two, Nakum still in the
lead with three.
>> Good job, baby.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Men on men.
We have Judd, Bobby Jon and
Blake for Nakum, taking on
Jamie, Brian and Gary for Yaxha.
Go!
Jamie has it.
Passes quickly to Gary.
Blake intercepts it.
Bobby Jon has it.
>> Bobby, throw it, throw it!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon throws
ahead to Blake, but it's short.
Gary's going to get it.
Gary tries to use the net.
Brian has it.
Jamie under the goal.
Yaxha scores!
We're tied three-three.
You guys are playing great.
This round is two women and one
man for each tribe.
It's Danni, Cindy and Brandon...
taking on Amy, Lydia and Rafe.
Go!
Ball is live.
Rafe has it.
Rafe fighting to keep his tribe
alive.
To Lydia, who fights off Cindy.
Lydia's ball.
Cindy tries to steal it.
Rafe and Brandon fighting for
it.
Brandon has it.
Brandon throws it down the
court.
Danni has it.
Danni scores for Nakum!
Nakum leads 4-3.
Everybody tired.
Hard to run on the net.
It's 114 degrees.
We're back to women.
Cindy, Margaret and Danni
taking on Brianna, Steph and
Lydia.
If Nakum scores, they win
immunity.
>> Do you hear me?
Do you know what a pick is?
>> PROBST: Let's go.
We're not resting.
>> Good job, guys!
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Ready?
Go!
Steph and Danni mixing it up
again.
Steph has it.
>> Go, Steph!
>> PROBST: Looking for somebody
to throw to.
>> Move, Brianna!
>> Bri, you got to move!
>> PROBST: Steph tied up already
with Danni.
Got to get rid of that ball.
Somebody got to get open.
Danni and Steph going at it.
Good, clean contact.
Lydia trying to get to the ball.
>> Bri, try and move!
>> PROBST: Brianna got to get
open.
>> Brianna, why ain't you
moving?
I want to see you hustle! God!
>> PROBST: Danni not giving up
on that ball.
Lydia has it.
Margaret steals it, tosses to
Cindy.
To Danni.
Steph tries to steal it.
Danni under the rim.
She's got a height advantage.
Danni scores for the win!
( cheering )
Nakum wins immunity!
>> Yeah, baby!
Come here, girl!
>> PROBST: Great final point.
Well played.
Nakum, who wants it?
Great effort in unforgiving
heat.
You have immunity.
No Tribal Council tonight.
>> Nakum!
>> PROBST: Yaxha, it has been a
tough first eight days out here
for everybody.
Gonna get a little tougher for
you guys tonight.
Tribal Council, you will vote
somebody else out of this game.
I'll see you there.
Head on out.
>> Yeah, here we go again.
I'm on this tribe that doesn't
seem to be too good at winning
in the beginning, and someone
sprains their ankle.
It's horrible.
I've already been here.
I've already done this.
I can't do it again.
I've only dehydrated like that
once in my entire life.
I was trying not to cry 'cause
I wanted to hold all the water
in.
>> Steph, don't be mad at
yourself.
We got to keep positive, you
know what I mean?
>> I'm frustrated because we
have Amy, she's got all the
strength in the world, and she
can't run.
And we have Brianna who's a
makeup artist.
After the first round, she's
like this-- her head's
completely up her butt.
I have to literally pull it out.
I'm like, "Dude, it's too early
in the game-- what are you
doing?"
Then we have a fish monger, who
I do love dearly because she
tries her best, but she's
really not athletic at all.
Part of me just wishes, like,
why, why, just once can't I
just be on a great tribe?
I want to see her.
Oh, my God, Amy.
>> It's good, it's all good.
I can feel it falling off.
I love this!
Snap, snap.
>> Did you hear it snap?
>> Oh, yeah, I snapped both
sides.
>> I rolled my ankle the
first game I went out there.
It's swollen, but it's
definitely something I can live
with.
I'm not going to, you know,
give up.
I got to make sure my team
knows I'm going to be all right.
>> High-five, baby, gimme some.
Don't worry. Hey...
>> All right.
>> And be honest with us, too.
>> I'm fine.
My ankle would have to be
falling off before I ever quit.
It might be a little painful,
but it's going to be fine.
>> Two of our girls don't
have a clue.
>> I explained what a pick was,
and they didn't do it.
>> Lydia has never played a
sport in her life.
Our team is totally down,
because we got two people
that never played a sport in
their life in Lydia and Brianna.
Amy sprained her ankle.
With these challenges, if you
had a sprained ankle, it would
be tough, so, uh, that's
big, 'cause we need to win.
>> Jamie, you know I gave it my
heart.
>> I know, I saw you.
You were out there hustling.
>> She knows she's done.
>> 'Cause I had a feeling it
would have been a toss between
me and her.
>> We're going to Tribal Council
tonight to vote Brianna out.
She's done.
Brianna's last day on
Survivor is tonight.
Day eight.
Well, that girl makes me sick.
She was leaning on a pole.
Literally, leaning on a pole.
You don't do that.
There's three people out there,
they're all busting ass.
You know, they're all working
hard and then, she's leaning
against the pole.
So there were only two people
out there working so hard.
She won't say anything to me
because she knows I'll tell her
right to her face.
I'm going to vote her off.
Everybody knew from day one, I
don't like Brianna.
She annoys me.
Not my type of girl.
I like them crazy and pretty.
She's neither.
>> Like you said, she probably
knows herself, huh?
>> She'll try to fight it,
but there's nothing she can do.
>> I love this game.
Why would I be here if I didn't?
>> Obviously.
>> Why would I be here if I
didn't think I could?
>> Right.
>> I'm here because I can.
>> I know you can.
>> I feel scared because the
weak link today was probably me,
and then I know Jamie and Lydia
would have me out of here if
they could.
I'm voting for Lydia because
when I talk to people, I look at
them in the eyes.
>> Right.
>> I've never seen her eyes.
She doesn't like me anyway.
>> Lydia? Really?
>> Mm.
>> Why?
>> I can tell.
I told you I'm good at reading
people.
>> Yeah, you did tell me that.
>> My vote tonight is based on
who I can trust and who I've
built relationships with, and I
haven't built that bond with
Lydia.
>> Is that too tight?
>> Let's go.
>> From now on, it's all
about who's athletic or not.
We can't lose anymore.
You can have all the heart in
the world, but if you can't
hang, you're lost.
There's no doubt out here right
now athletic ability means the
most.
>> PROBST: Welcome back to
Tribal Council.
Steph, is it too early to ask if
this is feeling a little
familiar, a little deja vu?
>> I'm having some horrible
flashbacks, that's for sure,
just that feeling again of
losing, and having to come here,
and having to get rid of another
person.
It makes me sick.
>> PROBST: At today's immunity
challenge, there were times
where it seemed like you were
looking around going, "Give me
some help here."
>> Yeah, I was completely
frustrated today during the
challenge, and, you know, I was
out there with Lydia and
Brianna, and, you know, they
haven't really played sports,
and they didn't know what a pick
was, and it's frustrating but
they were doing their best, and
obviously our best was not good
enough because we got beat.
>> PROBST: Brianna, is it fair
to come down on you because you
didn't know what a pick was?
>> I don't think anyone was
coming down on me for not ever
playing basketball and not
knowing the terminology.
I gave it my best, honestly, I
did.
>> PROBST: Lydia, I'll give it
to you, you were trying.
I don't know if you were much
more effective than Brianna was.
What do you think?
>> Well, Jeff, I sucked today.
But, you know, I was in there,
and I was doing my best.
Anything that would help the
tribe, grabbing the ball,
stealing from it, anything.
And I just put my heart into it,
and never gave up.
>> PROBST: Brian, you think this
tribe's out-matched?
>> The other tribe is extremely
athletic, perhaps more athletic
than we are, but we have
determination and will, and we
really are not out-matched in
how much we like each other.
I can't imagine the other tribe
being as unified as we are.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about the
wear and tear from today's
challenge.
Amy, I noticed when you came in,
you were hobbling a little bit.
>> When I first went out there,
I just turned my ankle.
But I didn't break it, so I'm
good to go.
>> PROBST: Gary, when you see
some of these injuries, does it
go through your head, you know,
we got to keep the strong, got
to get rid of the weak?
>> Well, we're definitely at a
point right now, Jeff, that
athleticism is big.
The reality is, if you can't
help us in the challenges, it's
going to hurt us as a team and
we're not going to get anywhere.
>> PROBST: Amy, you come in
here, you're injured.
All we talked about tonight is
physical, physical, physical.
How frustrating would it be to
go out number three?
>> It would be frustrating
because it would have to be
because they think I'm injured,
but it's not that serious.
So don't make the mistake.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Lydia, you're up.
>> Lydia, you have not once
looked me in the eye when I've
spoken to you or even attempted
at conversing.
>> You're a girlie-girl, you
need to go back to the shopping
mall when you leave the jungle.
>> I have to do what's right for
this tribe right now.
We've got to win immunity.
I can't be on the losing streak
anymore.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Brianna.
Lydia.
Two votes Brianna, one vote
Brianna.
That's three for Brianna.
Four votes Brianna.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala...
Brianna. That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Brianna, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> You guys are strong.
Kick some Nakum butt.
>> Brianna, sweetheart.
>> See ya, Bri.
>> PROBST: Well, we're only
eight days in, but when it comes
to Tribal Council, your strategy
seems clear: keep the strong,
vote out the weak.
But in a game this
unpredictable, voting based
solely on physical strength can
be risky.
See how it plays out.
Grab your torches.
Head on back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor... Yaxha has a deadly
visitor.
>> It's definitely dangerous,
there's no doubt about that.
>> PROBST: Misery plagues Nakum.
>> This place changes you out
here, just, you know, completely
wears you down.
>> PROBST: And the game is taken
to a new level.
>> Oh, my God!
>> It is survival of the fittest
out there.
And I was the weakest link.
You've got to be athletic to be
out here, and I gave it my all,
I tried my hardest.
I am an athletic person but not
as athletic as these people.
These are strong people.
I was only here for eight days
but it was the best eight days
of my life.
The toughest but the best.