>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor... Gary, Danni and
Bobby Jon found themselves on
the outside of the alliance of
six.
>> If it was the other way
around, they'd be doing the same
thing.
>> Yeah.
(chuckling)
>> PROBST: So the search for the
hidden immunity idol
intensified.
>> We need the immunity idol
now-- we need it right now.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the survivors
competed for a variety of meals.
First place, steak and lobster.
(gasping)
>> Man!
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winner of this challenge gets
one clue to the location of the
hidden immunity idol.
Judd dominated the challenge,
winning the best meal.
>> Wow.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Judd, steak and
lobster.
Also, a clue to the hidden
immunity idol.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: The next day, Judd
shared the clue with Stephenie.
>> "It's not buried or
concealed, nor directly on the
ground."
>> Gotta be like in a tree.
>> PROBST: And then he lied to
the others about the idol's
possible location.
>> It is totally on the ground.
I don't have a problem lying to
the other guys at all.
That's what the game is about,
man.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, Jamie's
paranoia annoyed even his
closest allies.
>> He seems like a loose cannon,
and I feel like he can ruin our
entire plan.
>> PROBST: But at the challenge,
Jamie won immunity and calmed
his nerves.
Jamie wins immunity.
>> Good job, Jame!
>> PROBST: Back at camp, the
alliance of six targeted Gary.
>> He's a huge physical threat.
He's just always, like, in game
mode.
>> PROBST: Knowing he was in
trouble, Gary continued to
search for the hidden immunity
idol and made an interesting
discovery.
>> I think it's pretty amazing
that Judd told everybody the
clue that it's on the ground.
I wonder why he's looking in
trees.
There's no doubt in my mind that
Judd's lying.
>> PROBST: When it was time for
the vote at Tribal Council...
If anybody has found the
immunity idol, now is the time
to bring it up.
>> Oh, my God!
Gary...
>> Oh, man!
>> PROBST: ...Gary caught his
tribe off-guard when he revealed
that he had found the idol.
With Gary suddenly safe, Bobby
Jon was voted out.
Bobby Jon, the tribe has spoken.
>> Thank you very much.
>> PROBST: Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> Well, we're gonna have a
fire, still.
Congratulations, Gar.
>> Gary, where'd you find it?
>> Hey, thanks, man.
>> Where did you find it?
>> At the, uh, Mayan worship
ciba tree.
I went to Tribal Council, and I
had found the small immunity
idol in the woods, and they had
to change their votes, because
they couldn't vote for me.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Did you... did you find it on
the first day or more recently?
>> Where's the trees the Maya
used to worship at?
>> I don't know.
>> I think Gary is shady.
Everybody else thinks he's a
good guy, but I don't think he
really is.
>> I don't care.
It's one vote.
Whoop-di-doodle.
Every time we get back from
Tribal Council, Jamie picks some
kind of argument with somebody.
He came to me and said, "You
know who wrote your name down?"
And I'm like, "Well, yeah, Gary
wrote my name down."
He just is trying to make me
have some kind of bitter
feelings towards Gary when I
didn't.
And then it seemed like he was
mad at me because I wasn't
getting mad.
>> I'm not playing into
anybody's game.
>> I got one vote. Whoop-di-doo.
>> Yeah, how's that playing into
somebody's game?
>> I don't even care.
It's like I don't care.
He doesn't even think before he
starts an argument, and then ten
minutes later, he starts talking
to Gary.
None of it made sense whatsoever
to anybody.
>> Well, Gary would lie when...
I tell you we were voting for
Brandon, he goes, "Yeah, you'll
vote for Brandon, too, and then
you'd vote for me?"
Was that a lie?
>> That'd be a lie that I
told... I never told you I was
voting for Brandon.
>> But I thought I told you
right here that I was like,
"We're voting for Brandon."
And you said... you said, uh...
"Okay, whatever," you said,
"Yeah, well, that's fine."
You'll vote for Brandon and then
you vote against me.
>> I don't think so.
>> Obviously, me and you are
going to have to fight this
whole thing now.
>> We don't need to fight.
I'm just...
>> Well, obviously, 'cause
you're calling me a liar and I
don't like it.
>> I did not just call you a
liar.
Maybe you just don't hear very
well.
>> I didn't really hear anybody
say you lied, though.
What are you talking about?
>> I know I'm just saying...
Dude, let's just drop it.
No one said I lied.
>> Jamie and Gary had a little
fall-out, because I guess Jamie
thinks Gary is a liar somehow.
I-I don't... I didn't see Gary
lying.
I-I think Jamie sometimes, he
just says things because he says
it.
>> Seriously, though, Gary, I
really thought, you know, you
said what you said, you know?
>> You know, Jamie, you're gonna
think what you want to think,
okay?
>> Yeah, and you're going to
think what you want to think.
>> You got that right.
>> Come on, Jamie, forget about
it.
>> I'll forget about it, but I'm
mad, too, Gary.
Don't worry about it.
>> What's that?
>> I'm mad, too, just like you.
>> I'm not mad.
>> I don't think he's mad
either, Jame.
I'm... I don't know.
>> I'm just gonna drop it.
>> It just seems like you're
starting to instigate...
>> Just drop it.
>> All right. Good, man.
That's what I want you to do,
man-- I don't think he's mad.
Emotionally, I guess this game
might be taking a toll on him,
and he really, psychologically,
he's losing it.
(chuckles)
(roars)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
And then there were eight.
Four men, four women.
Today's challenge is for reward.
Here's how it works.
You will be divided into two
teams-- one pair of men, one
pair of women on each team.
Each pair will be attached by a
rope.
Moving one pair at a time, you
will race through a deep mud
pit, as well as a series of
obstacles.
You'll go over the first
obstacle, under the second, over
the third obstacle.
At the end, you'll find pots
filled with corn.
Grab a pot and head back over
the same obstacles.
Once you make it back to your
mat, empty your corn into your
finished pot while the other
pair heads out.
The first tribe to fill their
pot to the white line wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: The winning team will
leave here via helicopter.
You'll be taken to a beautiful
private home, get a shower.
(squeals)
And wash your clothes.
Then pajamas, because you're
spending the night.
In the morning, you'll awake to
the smell of Folgers coffee.
>> Ooh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: Reenergize you,
rejuvenate you for these last
few days.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Let's draw for teams
and get started.
All right, we have our two
teams.
Jamie and Rafe, Cindy and Lydia
taking on Gary and Judd, Steph
and Danni.
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, guys!
Come on, guys!
Good job. Good job. Good job.
Together, together.
>> PROBST: Both guys heading
over at the same time.
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: Got to go under the
second obstacle.
Jamie dives right in.
Rafe dives in.
Gary and Judd, everybody
getting muddy.
Jamie and Rafe with a bit of a
lead.
Getting to their first pot of
corn and heading back.
Judd and Gary right behind them.
Now is where strategy comes in.
Gonna have to work together.
Rafe over first.
Jamie hands the pot to him.
Judd over first.
Gary hands the pot to him and
loses some corn.
>> Watch the corn.
>> PROBST: Rafe and Jamie with
the lead.
>> Guys.
>> PROBST: Gary and Judd, trying
to hang on.
>> Guys, come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Rafe and Jamie
protecting that corn.
Go.
>> Go, Lydia, Lydia!
>> PROBST: Cindy and Lydia on
the course.
Gary and Judd falling further
behind.
>> Come on, come on, Gary.
>> PROBST: Gary and Judd are
back. Stephenie and Danni are
out.
They've got some time to make
up.
Cindy and Lydia clearing the
last obstacle.
Lydia hurdles herself over.
Steph and Danni sliding under
the second obstacle.
Lydia and Cindy coming back with
the second pot, trudging through
the mud.
>> Come on, girls.
>> PROBST: They've got a decent
lead.
>> Go.
>> PROBST: Danni and Steph make
it to their second pot.
>> Keep going, guys.
You're doing well.
>> PROBST: Lydia and Cindy
trying to do the handoff.
That pot is heavy.
>> Come on, come on, come on.
>> Go, Danni. Go, Danni.
>> PROBST: Danni using those
long arms.
Lydia struggling.
That mud is deep!
>> Lydia, come on.
>> Come on, come on, come on,
come on.
>> PROBST: Danni and Steph
closing the gap.
>> You can do it, Lydia.
You can do it.
>> PROBST: Lydia has got to
touch the mat before you can go.
Danni and Steph have taken over.
They're passing Lydia with their
second pot.
Go!
Gary and Judd now with the lead.
Lydia really slow.
Go!
>> Good job, good job!
>> PROBST: Jamie and Rafe trying
to make up a lot of time.
Jamie throws himself over.
Rafe right behind.
>> Come on, guys!
>> PROBST: They're moving
quickly, diving under the second
obstacle.
They're making up a lot of time
very fast.
They've tied it up.
We're dead even.
Jamie and Rafe heading back.
Judd and Gary right behind them.
>> Good job, guys, keep moving.
>> PROBST: It's a long race.
Anything could happen.
Can't slow down now.
>> Gary, don't spill any.
>> All right.
>> Nice, Gar. Come on, Gar.
>> PROBST: Jamie and Rafe are
back with their third pot.
Touch that mat.
Go, Lydia.
Go, Cindy.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Got to hit the mat,
both of them.
Steph and Danni back out on the
course.
Cindy and Lydia, you're going to
have to move.
Danni and Stephenie now with the
lead.
Lydia really slowing them down.
You're gonna have to move,
Lydia.
Dig deep. Let's go.
>> Keep going, guys.
>> One, two, three, jump.
>> PROBST: One more pot of corn
might do it for Danni and Steph.
>> All right, we only need one
more.
>> One more.
>> PROBST: They've got their pot
and they're heading back.
Lydia still struggling.
>> I can't get my feet up.
>> Go, Danni.
>> PROBST: A big reward at
stake.
>> That's your job.
>> PROBST: Night away from camp.
Food, clean clothes.
Cindy and Lydia not quitting.
Let's go, women. Move!
Danni and Steph with...
Steph falls down.
Gotta get that corn in there to
count.
Will it be enough?
Yes!
(screaming)
Danni, Steph, Gary, Judd win
reward.
>> Good job!
We're still going to finish.
Let's go.
>> It's a done deal.
>> Oh!
>> Let's finish.
>> It's just worth doing right.
>> We're not quitting.
Let's... come on!
Come on, let's go.
>> They already won, Jamie.
There's nothing we can do about
it.
>> Okay, fine.
(speaking indistinctly)
>> PROBST: You guys ready?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Hit it.
>> Guys, day 25 is the best day
so far.
>> We're covered in mud.
>> One of the best days of my
life.
>> Me, too.
>> Just to get away from camp
was enough.
It was my first time actually in
a helicopter, so that was an
awesome experience in itself.
>> We're going to a mansion, you
guys.
How weird is it going to feel
being in a bathroom and looking
in the mirror?
>> Oh, that's right, the mirror.
>> I don't need that.
I don't want to look.
>> Oh, you guys, how amazing.
>> Oh, this is so beautiful!
>> Hi!
>> Hey!
We're home!
>> Greetings. Welcome.
>> The helicopter dropped us off
not too far from the house, and
you were greeted by this dude,
Louie.
>> This is my house, and this is
your casa.
>> We were filthy, man, full of
mud.
>> Okay, look at the pool.
>> Oh, look at the food.
(yelling)
>> Oh, nice.
>> This pool is unbelievable!
>> He took us down to the pool
area, where we all showered up.
>> Eww!
(giggling)
>> I would not have rather gone
on that reward with any other
people than those three that I
was with.
>> Two hot girls getting in the
shower together.
>> I-I wouldn't go that far, not
right now.
Danni and I are, like, really
similar.
She's a cool chick.
(screaming)
And Gary is just an awesome,
genuine guy.
And Judd and I have been buds
since the day I met him.
>> I'm just taking all my
clothes off, everything.
>> Really?
>> Yep.
(bird cawing)
>> What are you doing, Judd?
(giggling)
>> It's all right.
It's coming off.
(laughing)
>> It was definitely the best
foursome out here that I could
have gone on this most amazing
reward with.
This is more like very fancy
hors d'oeuvres.
Oh, lobster.
>> There you go.
>> Oh, it's a jalapeño!
We ate so much!
Oh, there's a lot of meat in
here.
Did I do well, or am I missing
out, like still on a bunch of
it?
>> No, you're doing good.
>> I love to eat, but Stephenie
eats even more than I do.
>> Whoa!
>> It's good, isn't it?
I haven't had a chance to get
to know her, and I think the
reward helps a lot.
I do feel bad that they're
back there.
>> Lydia, she was so down on
herself, I can't even imagine
today how she feels.
>> Oh...
>> My sincere apologies to you
guys, though, man.
You guys were ahead.
You and Jamie were ahead of-of
Gary and Judd.
You were!
>> Yeah, but i-it doesn't
matter, Lydia.
>> A bath, a nice bath and
coffee in the morning and
pancakes with syrup.
>> I don't need to hear it.
>> And a helicopter ride.
>> Yeah, I'm a little sad about
the helicopter ride.
(laughing)
>> I know we can get there if
you just... if you... if you
trust me.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Okay. I feel good about that,
then.
>> Well, can you swear like...
we'll go to the final three
together?
Because I will give you my word,
and I know I can pull it.
>> I don't know.
Like, I don't feel good about
giving you my word as a man if
I'm not like 100% on it.
Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah, yeah, why aren't you
100% about it? Like...
>> Well, because I haven't
thought about it at all.
>> You think about it.
>> Yeah, let me... 'Cause I-I...
You know, I'm not just going to
sit here and swear to you after,
like, five minutes of thinking
about it.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> I've almost given up trying
to understand Jamie's strategy
in this game.
I think that Jamie is just kind
of losing it, almost, in terms
of paranoia.
Like he's just letting the game
really, really get to him, and
he is constantly freaked out.
>> Here, I'll make an easy swear
for you.
Do you want to just swear the
top six right now?
>> I already have.
>> Okay, well I...
>> I already told you yesterday.
>> I won't sucker you.
Yeah. (chuckles)
>> I feel like my family at
Christmas-- we're all wearing
the same pajamas.
>> What a great feeling.
It's just like, just rejuvenated
me and everybody else with me.
There's no doubt that this would
be a good time to try and make
some ties with Stephenie and
Judd.
If they shut me down, they shut
me down.
But, uh, I've got to try because
I'm the next to go if-if they
don't change.
>> Okay.
>> Hard question.
>> My whole thing with you...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...and my whole thing with
Danni has been I want to take
the strongest four to the final
four...
>> Yeah.
>> ...so nobody slides by...
>> Right, and he said that since
day one.
>> ...with-with good attitudes,
that work hard in camp and
that are great competitors.
The play was, "Hey, I want the
best in the finals so you're
winning against the best."
And I-I don't know what they're
thinking.
But, uh, all's I could do is
plant a seed.
If Lydia goes to the final two,
guess who's winning?
>> She'll win.
>> Lydia.
>> Of course.
>> We know that.
>> If Cindy goes to the final
two, guess who's winning? Cindy.
>> We know that.
>> And-And do they deserve it?
>> I'm fine with that logic--
like to be the best, beat the
best.
But then at the same time, I
have such a good thing going.
It's kind of iffy.
So I'm not... really not sure
if we're going to go with that.
But it's a good idea.
>> Let me ask you this, then.
In a perfect world...
>> Yeah.
>> ...numbers aside, in this
game who would be the next
person you guys would want to
vote out?
>> There's no doubt who I'd vote
out.
>> Me, too. Jamie.
>> Well, who would it be?
>> Jamie.
>> Because of his attitude?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Bonding with Gary and Danni
is not going to affect my game,
because I know what my game plan
is.
But it's nice to get to know
somebody different who you
never met before.
>> I love Guatemala right now.
(chuckling)
>> Good night, Judd.
>> Good night, Gary.
Good game, man.
>> Yeah. You, too.
>> Sometimes this game affects
your heart a little bit.
Sometimes it kind of wrenches it
a bit.
And getting rid of those two
is... you know, that's gonna be
a little heart-wrenching.
But that's just the way the game
is, man.
If I want to go further in this
game, the threats gotta go.
>> Ooh, Nelly!
Smell that, baby?
>> So good!
>> Oh!
>> Oh, look at that, man!
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> When we got up this morning,
we could smell coffee.
It was so refreshing to smell
coffee, rather than the smell of
the jungle every morning when we
get up.
>> It's all crystally.
>> (squeals): So exciting!
>> Oh, you're a big coffee fan,
Dan, huh?
>> Well, I drink it a lot in the
mornings when I have early
mornings.
There was like six different
flavors of Folgers coffee.
And we tried all of them.
>> Oh, my God!
Oh, let's sit down.
>> Oh, man!
>> Where do you want to sit?
Hey!
>> What's up?
>> Louie!
>> Good morning.
>> What's going on?
>> Actually, I'm bringing a
little present.
>> Okay.
>> Oh!
>> Enjoy it.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you, Louie.
>> Look like videotapes.
>> Stop it.
>> Mm-mmm.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Are they?
>> Lou, our little buddy, comes
over and gives us a present.
Open it up, it's videotapes from
home.
>> Stephenie.
>> I told my family I wouldn't
cry.
>> If we didn't get any food or
shower or nothing and just got
the videotapes, I would have
been completely satisfied.
It was just the icing on the
cake.
>> Well, I'm at Grandma's...
>> Hey!
>> ...and I love you.
>> Then the tapes come out.
Ooh! That was sweet.
>> I'm cooking up some hot dogs.
>> Oh, no.
(thud)
>> Whoa, hey, easy there.
>> Hi, honey.
>> Oh, my gosh
>> I miss you very, very much.
Life is very, very, very boring
without you.
>> My wife, my daughter, my mom,
my nieces, my sister and my
brother-in-law.
>> We miss you, but...
have a nice cold beer and a fat
T-bone waiting for you when you
get home.
>> Better than steak and eggs
any morning, man.
(howls)
(screams and laughter)
>> Hi, Danni, it's your mom, of
course.
I love you so much.
Boy, do we miss you.
The two most important men in
your life would like to say
hello to you.
>> Hondo.
>> Hey, Danni, it's your old
buddy, Hondo.
Boy, I sure miss you.
>> My family, I knew, would be
fine.
I just wanted to see my dogs and
make sure they were okay.
And they look like they've been
well fed, so...
>> I'll be talking to you soon.
Love you, Danni. Bye.
>> Aw...
>> Whoo...
>> Oh...
>> Hi, Aunt Stephenie.
>> How are you?
Hopefully, the bugs aren't
biting too bad.
>> And I hope you're all right.
>> Yes, we do.
>> Bye-bye.
(blows kiss)
>> Kisses!
>> Go, Jets.
(shouting)
>> There was four videotapes in
there of our families.
We watched the videos and
just had a great time.
I saw everybody else's family,
which was really neat.
'Cause they're always talking
about them.
So now you can connect names
with faces.
>> Hey, Dad, hope everything is
going good.
I'm getting ready for
California, and I will talk to
you when you get back.
>> I'm definitely not very good
at this, but I just want to tell
you that I love you and miss you
and we'll see you soon.
>> I'm an emotional wreck
anyways when it comes to
anything family.
And not seeing them for 25 days
and then seeing my kids and my
wife, it was phenomenal.
>> Hey, Dad.
>> Aw...
>> Hope you haven't got hit in
the head with a coconut yet.
But if you have, hi, my name is
Jamie and I'm your daughter.
>> You got muscles on top of
your muscles and muscles on top
of those muscles...
>> It was the best reward
challenge prize that we possibly
could have had.
>> ...beat you up.
(laughing)
>> Two weeks, you'll be home
in two weeks.
>> Well, we're in the real world
now.
>> Yeah, back to the hellhole.
>> Here they come.
>> Hey.
>> Is this them?
>> Hi!
>> Hey.
>> Hey, guys.
>> Welcome back.
>> We didn't bring food, so
don't get too excited.
>> We made a little basket of
different coffees, and I was
kind of hiding it.
And I mean Cindy, she's a huge
coffee fan and her eyes just lit
up.
>> Coffee!
>> Oh, Cindy!
>> Oh, my gosh!
Stephenie pulls out this basket,
and it's got, like, a dozen or
more little Folgers coffee
singles, like little tea bags.
I just thought that is the most
perfect thing that they could
possibly walk into camp with.
>> We thought you're gonna just
flip.
>> I cannot even believe it.
I mean, it could have been a
basket of cookies, it could have
been a basket of rolls,
whatever.
But it was basket of coffee.
>> Not a lot.
>> Ooh, you guys smell good.
>> How was... did you get a nice
bed to sleep in?
>> I slept on the floor.
>> You didn't sleep on the bed?
>> The only person I was really
concerned about was Jamie.
I didn't know how he would react
to... to me and Steph going
away, because I didn't want
Jamie to feel like we made any
alliances with Danni or Gary,
which we didn't, so...
It was cool.
>> I know, bud.
What's up, Gary?
>> How's it going?
>> Good. How was your...
How was the food?
>> It was all right.
>> Good food?
>> You know, I don't know if
it's too late, but Judd really
seemed to have fun.
Danni and Stephenie hit it off
immediately.
I don't know how sincere they
were, but-but I made the pitch
to them.
And they're either going to take
it or they're not.
So, if I don't win immunity
on the next challenge and it
doesn't change, I'll be gone.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Good morning, guys.
>> Good morning.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Jamie, give it up.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
Ready to get to the challenge?
Here is how it works.
You will be attached to one long
rope, which is threaded through
three obstacles.
You will have to climb over,
crawl under, maneuver around as
you race through these
obstacles.
The first four to the finish
move on to the final round.
For the final round, you will
once again be attached to one
rope.
Only this time, the obstacle is
three levels high, and that will
seriously complicate things.
First person to finish wins
immunity.
Guarantees themself a one-in-
seven shot at $1 million.
We'll draw for position and
we'll get started.
Here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
Gary wasting no time.
Rafe doing well.
Cindy right in there.
Danni trailing behind.
Judd having trouble figuring it
out.
He's bringing up the tail.
Lydia throwing herself over this
obstacle.
Does not want to be last again.
Gary the first to move on to the
second obstacle.
Cindy and Steph are neck and
neck in second place.
Cindy moves on to second
obstacle.
Steph right behind.
Rafe, Jamie fighting for that
fourth spot.
Rafe now at the second pole.
It's Gary and Cindy, Steph and
Rafe now looking to be the final
four.
I forgot about Danni.
Danni is on the ground, almost
out of sight.
Gary has moved on to the third
stage, the big lead.
Four people are moving on to the
next round.
Immunity at stake.
Cindy having a little trouble
with the second pole.
Not as easy as it looks.
Rafe picking up some ground.
Danni, Judd, Lydia are falling
out of this competition.
Jamie has moved on to the third
stage.
It's Gary, Rafe and Jamie on the
last stage.
Cindy and Steph fighting for
that fourth spot.
27 days, taking its toll right
now.
Gary still in the lead.
Judd has given up.
>> I'm not giving up.
I'm-I'm trying to figure it out.
>> PROBST: Steph has moved on to
the third stage.
Cindy falling out of it.
She's got to get on to the third
stage to have a shot.
Gary ran into a bit of an
obstacle.
Rafe gaining some time.
Rafe now in the lead.
Gary falling back.
Jamie and Rafe now fighting it
out.
Gary trying to figure out where
he's stuck.
What happened?
Things were going smoothly.
He's not panicking.
Taking his time.
Cindy nowhere closer to that
third stage.
Rafe is good. He's moving on.
Three spots left.
Jamie looking good.
Steph making some progress.
But Gary is still stuck.
Jamie is across.
He's moving on.
Rafe and Jamie in this final
round.
Cindy moved on to the third
stage.
Two spots left.
Gary back on track now.
Easy to tie yourself up in a
knot.
Steph moving on to the final
round.
One spot left.
Who's it going to go to?
Cindy and Gary both want it.
It's going to be tight.
Cindy is moving.
Gary in the last leg.
Cindy right behind.
It is Cindy and Gary very close.
Gary hustling to get through
that last leg.
There it is, Gary and Cindy.
Cindy moving on to the finals...
>> Phew!
>> PROBST: ...edges out Gary.
It's Cindy, Steph, Jamie and
Rafe for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, girls.
>> PROBST: You now have three
levels gonna have to climb up,
back down.
Cindy takes a fall.
Steph, throwing herself through
the challenge.
First person to finish gets the
immunity necklace and is safe at
tonight's Tribal Council.
Cindy and Rafe, dead even.
When Cindy starts to move, she
flies.
Steph close behind.
Jamie trying to get back into
it; he's figured it out now.
Cindy now with a bit of a lead.
Rafe right behind, not giving
up, still very tight.
One slip-up can cost you.
Cindy moving quickly.
She's into the fourth section.
Rafe slowing down.
It's Cindy's to lose now.
Rafe trying to make up some
time.
Cindy flying through this
obstacle.
Rafe fighting to stay in it.
It's Cindy and Rafe right now,
immunity on the line.
Cindy is stuck.
Cindy has lost her lead.
Cindy now picks up.
Once again, it's going to be a
close finish.
Cindy and Rafe.
Rafe... wins immunity!
(applause)
>> Good job.
>> Thanks, guys.
>> PROBST: Rafe, come on over.
>> Good job, Rafe.
>> PROBST: Rafe is safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
One of you seven is going home.
Back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal
Council.
>> Good job, Rafe.
>> Thank you.
>> It's crazy.
Of the three immunities I have
competed in, I've won two and
finished second in one of them.
Um... you know, I just made
myself a huge threat in this
game.
And I think I am going to have
to change the way I am playing.
>> I got stuck, I couldn't fit
my shoulders through.
>> Well, you're-you're tall.
>> I got stuck.
>> I would've thought it would
have been terrible for you.
>> I didn't win immunity
challenge.
I was way out in the lead and
couldn't get my body through a
little hole.
So, that was tough.
But I gave it my best shot.
I went out fighting.
And you never know.
>> Huh?
>> Making sure we're all good.
>> Mm-hmm.
We're going to vote for Gary
tonight.
Jamie's just very paranoid.
I mean, he's not going anywhere.
He might get maybe...
one vote, from Gary.
And that's it.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I mean, I thought it was
actually a fun challenge, but...
>> I thought it was good.
>> Yeah.
>> Freaking workout.
My legs are killing me right
now.
>> My arms are.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I didn't win immunity
today; Rafe did.
But he is not the serious threat
right now; it's Gary.
And eventually, they're gonna
catch on that I'm the serious
threat.
So I'm trying to work it where
they, uh, keep the six that got
here together.
And I'm working that card a lot.
We're still sticking to the
plan?
>> As far as I know.
Haven't heard anything else.
Is there anything else for me to
know?
>> I just... I-I don't want to
go home tonight.
I'm sticking with the six, you
know?
>> We said we would.
I don't see...
>> Yeah.
>> It's working so far.
>> I know Lydia and Judd won't
change; I know Rafe pretty much
won't change.
You know, I just...
Sometimes I wonder what
Stephenie's thinking, you know?
Do you ever get like that or no?
>> Yeah, you got to wonder what
everybody's thinking.
But you know, we said we'd do
the six and it's working out for
us, so why screw it up now?
>> Good...
>> No reason.
>> I appreciate that a lot.
'Cause I'm-I'm kind of scared
now, just in case, you know...
>> For me personally, Jamie's
paranoia is just getting crazy.
He just doesn't know when to be
quiet.
It just seems ridiculous, and
it's getting old.
>> Sure.
>> Jamie is such a control
freak.
He'll come over and say, "Rafe,
let's go play Guatemancala,"
which has become his signal for
"Rafe, I need to talk to you
about the game."
So I have to play Mancala with
him every day.
>> I mean, like, I don't know
what to tell you.
You're constantly asking.
He's, like, "So you're sticking
with the six, right?
Are you going to stick with the
six?
You should stick with the six,
right?
I'm just worried that everyone's
not going to stick with the
six."
I'm like "Jamie, I'm sticking
with the six.
Like, if you ask me again I'm
going to die.
I'm going to throw these pieces
of corn at you.
I-I... You're driving me
insane."
>> Okay.
>> I don't know what to say, you
know, I mean...
It's a hard decision.
Jamie and I, we have been
together since day one.
So it's very, very difficult for
me to think about voting him
off.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Gary is a smooth operator.
>> I-I think we should do it.
>> Okay, that's what my heart
says, too.
>> What do you think, Lydia?
>> You guys want Jamie to go,
right?
>> PROBST: We will now bring in
the first member of our jury:
Bobby Jon, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Jury members are here to listen
in.
You're not to direct any
comments to them.
They're gathering information to
make a very big vote.
So, let's talk about the reward
first.
Steph, the biggest reward we've
had so far.
And did it give you time to bond
with Gary and with Danni and
with Judd?
>> Yeah, it absolutely did.
I mean, we just enjoyed each
other's company and just really
got to know each other.
And especially for Gary.
I mean, he almost went home the
day before.
So, you know, we really kind of
bonded.
So that was cool.
>> PROBST: Danni, do you feel
the same way?
>> Oh, yeah.
I mean, I haven't had a chance
to be on a team with
Stephenie, and Gary and Judd
hadn't had a chance, so it was
just nice to get to know one
another.
Um, 'cause we're pretty familiar
with everybody else.
>> PROBST: Judd, did you and
Gary bond?
>> Oh, man. Gary, to me, is just
an amazing person, man.
He's somebody that you want to
look up to, man.
I kind of keep my cool when he's
around.
You know, I try to be a man
myself, but sometimes I feel
like I'm a little kid at times.
But Gary, man, he's... he's a
man's man.
I got to give it to him, man.
Nothing but respect for him.
>> PROBST: Would that make it
more difficult to vote for him
tonight, or are you able to go
right back into game mode?
>> Oh, no. This, to me, is
probably going to be one of my
most difficult votes.
I mean, in order for me to move
on, you know, it has to be done.
I mean... it's not easy.
It's not going to be easy, but I
got to move on.
>> PROBST: Jamie, is there
anybody left that you would say,
"You know what, I wouldn't miss
them and I won't miss them when
they're gone"?
>> No, I-I couldn't say that
about anybody else on this
tribe.
I think everybody here has super
hearts and are super people.
It's just when you're out in
this jungle, you know, you can
go insane out here, I believe,
if you don't watch yourself.
It gets to you.
But all of these people here
have been really supportive and
really great.
And so, may the best man or
woman win.
>> PROBST: Gary, mentally, where
are you at in this game right
now?
>> You know, I think the most
important thing out here is a
positive attitude in any
survival situation.
And we are in a survival
situation.
You know, I'm weak.
You can't do the things you
normally do.
So I'm just trying to be upbeat
and just make it through every
day.
And what happens happens.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
the vote.
Rafe, you have individual
immunity.
If you want it, you can give it
to somebody you thought needed
it or keep it for yourself.
>> I'm going to keep it for
myself.
>> Rafe is the only one you
cannot vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Jamie, you're up.
>> I hope we can be friends one
day, but it's either you or me
tonight, buddy.
>> Jamie, I still think you got
a big heart, and I'd want you on
my team any day of the year.
>> Gary, thanks for sharing this
experience with me, buddy.
We got to let you go.
I don't want to, but...
Thanks for everything and God
bless you.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Gary.
Two votes Gary.
Jamie.
Two votes Gary, one vote Jamie.
Two votes Gary, two votes Jamie.
Jamie.
That's three votes Jamie,
two votes Gary.
Jamie.
Four votes Jamie.
The 11th person voted out of
Survivor Guatemala, Jamie.
Jamie, the tribe has spoken.
>> Blindsided-- nice.
Now that's how you vote somebody
out.
(mutters)
>> PROBST: Well, Jamie just gave
you the best advice anybody
could: blindsided.
Who you share information with
and what information you share
is critical if you want any shot
in this game.
Consider that a gift.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: Judd is left reeling
after Tribal Council.
>> I don't know what to say.
I mean, I wish somebody would
have told me.
It makes me wonder, from now on
what the hell is going on?
>> PROBST: And emotions run
high.
>> And I don't want to hear any
more about it...
>> Well, you say nothing's
personal.
Everything's personal, man.
>> You think this isn't going to
show me where your loyalties
lie?
You are sadly mistaken.
>> It really hurts that Lydia
voted against me because I took
her so far.
As much as I warned Lydia about
times she was in trouble, she
couldn't tell me I was in
trouble, so that's gonna be hard
for me to forgive her for that.
It hurts when you see good
people go bad, but that's how
the game plays.
You know, honesty is a huge
thing, and I don't think I ever