>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor:
>> Now that there are six of us
left, I'm next to have my head
chopped off.
>> PROBST: Danni felt vulnerable
but remained optimistic.
>> This perfect little alliance
is going to have to start
breaking up.
I'm definitely not going down
without a fight.
>> PROBST: Sold!
The survivors participated in an
auction.
>> $180.
>> $200.
>> Sold.
And Danni outbid the others for
a secret clue that could help
her at the next immunity
challenge.
It needs to remain sealed.
We'll deal with it when you get
to the next challenge.
>> Okay.
( gasping )
>> PROBST: The last item offered
up was an overnight visit with a
loved one.
>> $60, $70, $880.
>> PROBST: Judd bought a night
with his wife, Kristin.
Judd, you have purchased the
right to invite two other loved
ones to camp with you as well.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Yes!
>> Cindy, without a doubt, and
I'm going to take my Jersey girl
with me.
>> PROBST: Cindy's sister Mindy
and Stephenie's boyfriend
Michael joined them.
Danni, Rafe, and Lydia were
exiled from the group and forced
to spend the night at the old
Yaxha camp.
>> This is lake water that we
got boil.
>> PROBST: While the loved ones
got a taste of camp life.
At the old Yaxha camp, Danni and
Rafe strategized.
>> We just need to catch Judd in
some kind of lie, so that we can
show Steph...
>> The only person I really feel
like I can't trust now is Rafe.
I'm important to have around for
him because they have to see '05
as the threat.
>> PROBST: The next morning,
Danni, Rafe, and Lydia returned
to camp and the loved ones said
their good-byes.
>> Bye-bye, you guys!
>> PROBST: Before the immunity
challenge, Lydia tried to ally
herself with Judd, while Danni
listened in.
In a mental challenge for
immunity, Danni used her secret
clue from the auction.
>> "Switch positions with any
player."
I'm going to switch with Steph.
>> PROBST: The clue paid off
when Danni beat out Steph.
Danni wins immunity.
You are safe tonight at Tribal
Council.
Danni's next move was to target
Judd by exposing his earlier
conversation.
>> I'd like to believe Judd, but
he's already been caught in
quite a few lies, and Danni
really hasn't lied at all.
>> PROBST: Danni's maneuvering
worked.
Judd and Cindy were taken by
surprise when Stephenie, Rafe,
Lydia and Danni banded together
and voted out Judd.
>> Thanks, guys.
Hope you guys all get bit by a
freaking crocodile.
Scumbags.
>> PROBST: Judd, the tribe has
spoken.
Five are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( theme song playing )
>> It was just really hard for
me, because I had been really
close to him.
But as he spoke.
>> Scumbags?
>> Scumbags, and hopes we get
eaten by crocodiles.
I mean, he almost started to
turn into Jamie a little bit.
>> He was pissed.
>> Judd got voted out tonight,
completely blindsided.
Stephenie and Rafe broke that
alliance, and I had been praying
for a crack in that alliance.
>> Cindy, I wanted to tell you
so bad.
>> You didn't have to tell me,
but, you know, to talk to me,
and then you could tell by a
conversation with me, which way
I'm leaning.
I thought we were voting out
Lydia, and that was our plan
for, you know, the past few
days, but, apparently, I was not
privileged to the information.
>> Judd's gone tonight, and
you're still here.
Like, you know, I mean, it
wasn't like I was making a
decision whether to vote you
out.
>> I just don't want to follow
in Jamie and Judd's footsteps,
but the pattern makes me
nervous.
You didn't tell Judd that you
were voting out Jamie, and now
Jamie is gone, and then you
didn't tell me that you were
voting out Judd, and now Judd is
gone, so then where does that
put me?
Next thing you know, I'm going
to be gone.
>> No, it could be any of us.
>> I know it could be, but I see
a little pattern there, and it
makes me uncomfortable.
Judd is gone, and I'm still
here, so I'm going to have to
deal with it... move on.
>> How fitting is this that
you're the only guy left?
>> It's hilarious.
And the hardest survivor ever,
it's the gay guy and four women
in the final five.
>> All the boys pretty much are
on the jury.
>> I'm the last man standing.
I'm sitting around camp with
four girls, and I'm really
happy.
It's like Rafe's Angels around
camp.
>> Things we're not going to
miss about Guatemala.
>> Naked Judd.
( laughter )
It's kind of like when Judd is
voted out, that the cool kid
kind of left the class, and now
we can all be like a little
bit dorkier, a little bit more
fun.
( laughter )
>> Make yourselves cross-eyed.
>> Ooh, that's very disturbing.
( laughter )
>> I know.
>> No, not quite.
>> What am I doing?
>> You're just opening them
really wide.
You're like....
( chuckling )
>> Rafe, he's a real gentle type
of a male, and he fits right in
with us, so we're looking at him
as one of the girls.
>> Justin Timberlake was
Backstreet, right?
>> 'NSync.
>> He's hot.
>> Yeah, he is.
♪ My one desire
Tell me why... ♪
In all honesty, even though
these four women are here, and
they could easily vote me out,
on a close, personal level, I
have a really personal
friendship with all four of the
people left in this game.
And, you know, that's the thing
that I'm hoping will get me to
the end.
( gasps )
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Oh...
You guys!
Here, read it.
>> Shut the hell up!
Oh, God!
That's it.
>> That is insane, you guys.
>> One of us is going to own a
car today.
>> Oh, my God!
>> This might be one of the best
tree mails yet.
It looks like the reward is
going to be a car.
>> It's just a car key.
>> And I personally have never
had my own car.
So, I'm in desperate need of a
car.
>> Lydia, look.
>> And they're trying to win a
car.
>> My gosh!
I haven't really won anything,
so I just have this crazy
feeling that this might be my
opportunity.
This one's for my son.
He's 17 years old.
This is for him.
I'm going to have to work real
hard for it.
>> I know.
>> Could you imagine?
>> This is not a good time for
me to try to not chew my nails.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
>> Wow.
>> This is crazy.
>> PROBST: We haven't even got
to the challenge and everybody's
already smiling.
( laughter )
All right, today's challenge is
for reward, and it's called
"Second Chance," because that's
exactly what it is, a second
chance at some of the challenges
from the past.
On my go, all five of you will
race across a balance beam,
untying three sets of mckannas
as you go.
The first three to cross the
finish line with all of their
mckannas move to the next round.
For the next round, you will use
those mckannas to attempt to
break a single tile, 30 feet
away.
The first two to break their
tile, move on to the last round.
For the final round, you must
solve a puzzle based on the Maya
calendar.
Once you solve the puzzle, you
hop in the cart.
Use the machete to chop the rope
which will release the cart and
send you racing down to the
finish.
First one to the finish wins
reward.
I think you know what you're
playing for.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: 2006 Pontiac
Torrent.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: The winner gets the
car.
You will drive away and head
down to an archaeologist's camp,
where we've set up a barbecue
feast.
>> Oh, my God.
Steak, sausage, eggs, veggies, a
couple of bottles of rum.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: You will spend the
night, return to camp in the
morning.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
First three to cross the finish
line with all of their mckannas
moves on to the next round.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Steph off to a quick start.
Already untying.
Everybody at their first
mckannas.
Balance, patience; if you fall
off the beam, you must go back
to the start.
Steph, making good progress.
Steph and Cindy and Danni.
Danni almost falls off.
Rafe has his.
Lydia has hers.
Steph at work on the next set of
knots.
Lydia crawling up to it.
Steph has her second set of
mckannas.
Danni right behind.
Cindy right in it.
It's Steph, Danni, and Cindy.
Steph falls off.
She's got to go back to the
start.
It's now Danni and Cindy.
And here comes Rafe.
Lydia falls off, back to the
start.
Cindy teetering.
Hanging on.
Rafe falls off.
Rafe back to the start.
Suddenly Steph's back in it.
Three people moving on.
Cindy falls off.
She's got to go back to the
start.
Steph back in it.
Lydia falls off and back to the
start.
Danni on her last knot.
Steph getting close.
Danni has hers untied.
She's going to make a run for
it.
She's got to stay on.
Danni's across.
Danni moving on.
Cindy's across.
Cindy moving on.
There's one spot left.
It's Rafe and Steph.
Steph with a bit of a lead on
the knots.
Rafe catching up.
Steph has hers free.
Steph, third person moving on.
Here we go.
First two to break their tile
move on to the final round.
Ready, aim, fire!
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Danni nicks a tile.
Doesn't break it.
Ready, aim, fire!
Cindy, obliterates her tile.
Cindy moving on the to final.
Down to Danni and Steph.
Next one to break their tile
moves on to the final round.
Ready, aim, fire!
Steph breaks her tile!
Steph and Cindy in the final.
We are down to Cindy and Steph.
2006 Pontiac Torrent on the
line, along with a big feast and
a night away from camp.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Cindy has her bag open.
So does Steph.
Both Steph and Cindy working on
the puzzle.
It's based on the Maya calendar.
You should know that calendar by
now.
You've done this challenge
before.
Steph making good progress on
her puzzle.
Cindy right behind.
Cindy working on that outer edge
of the puzzle.
Steph working from left to
right.
Making some progress.
Two different strategies on
putting this puzzle together.
Cindy very close.
Cindy on her last piece.
She has it.
Cindy's good.
She's in her cart.
>> Go, Cindy.
>> PROBST: She has it!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Cindy with the ride
of her life.
Cindy wins reward!
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> PROBST: Here are the keys.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> PROBST: To the 2006 Pontiac
Torrent.
You've also won a barbecue
feast.
And the right to invite one
person to join you on that
feast.
But before you answer... you may
or may not know, but in ten
seasons of Survivor, the person
who has won the car reward has
never, ever won the game.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Some people, the
superstitious kind, believe it
is the curse of the car.
So, I'm going to give you a
chance to get rid of that curse
right now, perhaps change your
destiny in this game.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: If you want, you can
give up your car and instead
each of the other four will get
a Pontiac Torrent.
>> Oh!
Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh... my God!
>> You've got to be kidding me.
>> PROBST: What's it going to
be, Cindy?
>> I normally don't believe in
superstitions, but I also want
them to have cars.
I also believe in making the
impossible possible, which means
screw the curse.
I can win the car and the
million dollars if I play my
cards right and if I do my best.
>> PROBST: Tough decision.
You gotta make a decision right
now.
What's it going to be?
>> I think I'm going to say...
I would love to give everyone a
car... but I'm here to beat the
odds, and so far I have.
( clapping )
>> Good job, Cindy.
>> PROBST: Who's going on the
reward with you?
You will take one person with
you.
The other three will stay back
at camp.
>> Normally in the game of
Survivor, if you come in
second, it'll get you nothing,
but today it's gonna get
Stephenie a reward with me.
>> PROBST: Stephenie, come on
over.
>> Have fun, guys.
>> Thank you.
I would have kept the car.
>> PROBST: Cindy, go check out
your new car.
Steph, you're riding with her.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Cindy, this is beautiful!
Be happy!
>> There's no guarantees in this
game, and giving people cars
doesn't mean they're gonna say
give her a million bucks.
>> Exactly.
>> PROBST: Fire it up.
>> We love you.
>> Bye, guys.
>> A really nice car!
( clapping, cheering )
>> This s a freaking sweet car,
Cindy.
>> I'm just, like, looking
around.
My mind is still just reeling
that this is even, you know,
taking place, and I just won--
first of all, I won a reward;
second of all, I won a reward
that was a freaking car!
♪ Driving around in my
automobile... ♪
>> Stephenie was just like, oh,
my gosh, overwhelmed with
enthusiasm for me.
>> This is beautiful!
Well, this zookeeper does.
>> She seemed to really
appreciate what this meant to
me.
I don't think I've ever been
that happy in my whole life.
>> How cool was it to see three
chiquitas at the finish
line? Oh, my God!
>> Chicks rule.
>> It was awesome.
>> I was just like, man, chicks
rule in this game.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, look at the lake.
Love this.
>> My God!
>> I'm so happy for you.
So we pulled up to the
archeological site, and there
was an archaeologist guy sitting
there, waiting for us.
>> Hey, guys.
>> Hello.
>> My name is Federico Farson.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> And this is the Yaxha
Archaeological Campsite.
I know you're hungry and tired,
but we've got lots of good
things for you.
>> Yay!
>> Food over here.
There's meat,
there's vegetables, there's rum.
Enjoy it.
I'll be back in a while, you
know after you have...
>> Come have a drink with us.
>> Yeah, I will.
>> Thank you. Nice to meet you.
>> Oh, my God.
Gosh, look at all that meat.
More meat than we've seen in 30-
some days.
>> Yeah, it is.
I'm so excited.
To your new car.
>> Thank you.
>> Cheers to that.
>> Never in Survivor has the
winner of the car ever won the
million dollars.
So they, like, call it the
Survivor curse of the cars.
Oh, my gosh, they're going to be
so jealous, they're going to
vote us out right away.
It was really hard because you
look at all the four people,
and you're thinking, when in my
life will I ever have the
capacity to give four
people new cars?
Like, I don't know anybody who
has the ability to do that.
Maybe Oprah.
If you win, you win.
>> Yeah, why should you feel
bad?
>> I don't know.
>> I think at this point, there
are no guarantees.
They're not going to give you a
million dollars because you
gave them a car.
So I took the car, and I don't
think anybody was bitter about
it at all.
>> I was, like, shocked.
I just couldn't believe that
that was the decision Cindy
made.
For me, that didn't seem like a
choice.
It was, like, you have to give
the car to the four other
people.
Like, there was nothing else I
would have done.
Like, I never would have taken
the car for myself.
I was standing there, and I'm
going like, oh, my gosh.
This is so sad for Cindy.
She deserves that so much.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And now she has to give it
up, because there's, like, no
other choice.
>> Yeah, yeah, that's exactly
what I was thinking.
I was like, oh, no.
You know, I was just like, you
know, oh, my God.
I actually thought Cindy would
do it, because I would have done
it in a heartbeat.
Because you would have four
people who were very happy with
you.
>> In my mind I'm thinking:
"Cindy, keep the car, you
deserve it.
You won it rightfully," you
know...
>> She needed a car.
>> Yeah.
>> I was just thinking, like,
four people can have a car, or
one... you know what I mean?
I know that if Cindy had decided
to give the four of us cars,
there's no way on earth I could
vote her out at the next Tribal
Council.
But now you never know what's
going to happen.
>> My God, this is so good.
That steak is unreal.
That good?
>> Mmmm-hmmm.
( chuckles )
Hello there.
>> How was dinner?
>> It was so good.
There's so much to eat.
>> We have lots of leftovers to
drink.
>> Federico came back after we
had cooked our food, and he sat
down and told us story after
story about the Mayans and
the ruins and answered
questions.
>> They really ate that corn all
the time?
>> All the time.
Corn is the basic food of the
Maya then and the Maya now.
>> Oh.
>> He's a real-life
archaeologist, which to me, very
cool.
>> Yasha means green-blue.
>> That was our color, yeah.
>> And Yaxha means water.
So green-blue water is the lake
right there.
>> Oh, okay.
>> All the while, I'm listening
to his stories, and right behind
me, every time I turn my head,
out of the corner of my eye, I
can see this car sitting there
that's mine.
I get to keep that.
>> So nice to meet you.
>> Bye-bye.
>> Thank you so much.
♪ ♪
>> Look how cute that is.
Oh, my God!
Oh, there's candles!
And blankets.
>> How pretty is this?
>> Um, I've just been thinking,
I really like Danni, but I
really don't want to chance it.
>> And lose to her.
>> Right.
If she went further than me,
that would suck, or you or Rafe.
>> Danni?
>> Yeah, because, like, we were
the ones that came in with the
numbers.
>> And we had the chance to get
to get rid of her and we didn't.
>> A number of times.
I mean, all it would take would
be me, you, and Lydia, but I
would like to include Rafe.
>> I think he'd be willing
to go.
I mean, it guarantees you
another day in the game.
I was able to spend a lot of
time with Stephenie and find out
what the heck was going on.
If we beat each other, that's
one thing, but she would beat us
all.
>> And we'd look like total
idiots.
We came up with the concept that
Danni was our biggest threat at
this point.
So, we should try to take Danni
out next.
Danni is just like the rest of
us.
She's gonna come on stronger
by the day because the stakes
are higher.
>> Nobody promised her anything.
We'll bring it up to Rafe, see
how he feels.
>> I would think that Rafe would
understand someone as a physical
threat.
>> Yeah, well, Rafe's a smart
kid.
Hope he finally gets it.
>> Hi, guys!
>> Oh, my God!
( indistinct chatter )
>> So early.
>> Cindy, did you drive it okay?
>> Yeah, it drives so nice.
>> It drives so nice.
>> Like, I can't believe that
that car handles that way.
The suspension and everything is
so nice.
I mean, you barely even felt the
rocks.
I was just like, this is like a
freaking luxury vehicle.
>> I really never expected I
would own a brand-new vehicle in
my entire life.
Like, every time I go out to get
in it, anybody who's with me,
I'm just going to be, like, you
like my car?
I love the way the tires are
shaped, and I love the way the
taillights look.
>> That's why I asked.
It's cute that Cindy is
really, really excited about the
car, but at the same time, I
think it's grating on people a
little bit.
>> I've never really never for
once ever in my life ever
considered that I would own a
brand-new vehicle.
I mean, the thought never
crossed my mind.
>> You can only hear so much
about something that everyone
else could have had, too.
>> You never expect stuff like
that.
>> Like, if you can't read that
body language, um, no one
listening when you're talking
about the car, you know, it's
probably best to stop that talk.
>> There's no guarantee that
you're going to win.
I really don't think winning a
car has anything to do with it.
>> No.
>> You have a brand-new, nice-
smelling vehicle.
>> It was so unexpected.
They were excited to hear about
the car.
Everyone seemed to think that
choosing the car and the reward
for myself was the right thing
to do.
No one, um, seemed to have any
qualms about it at all.
>> She's so happy about the car.
I mean, that's all she talked
about was the car.
>> Really?
>> She felt bad.
Now, I'm like, why are you going
to feel bad?
Why are you going to give the
car up?
>> Yeah, well, see, Danni and I
both thought that she was.
>> So did I.
She was considering it.
>> I... I didn't-- Danni and I
both thought there wasn't any
other option than to give up the
car.
>> What do you mean?
>> Like, if they had asked me
that, like, there's no way I
would have kept it.
>> Really? Why?
>> No way.
Because it's like four of you
guys could have a car.
>> You thought you had to give
it up?
>> Not that you had to, but I
just... I would have.
>> Really?!
I didn't think anybody would
have.
That's a tough decision.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't think I would have
done it.
I could not believe he said, "I
would have gave the other four
the car."
I was like... no way.
Seriously, sometimes I just feel
like Rafe does try to play the
martyr a little bit.
That was like the first time
Rafe and I have ever disagreed
the whole game.
Wow, that's surprising.
I don't think I would have.
>> I would have in like a
heartbeat.
>> But a car when you don't have
one?
Lydia, you would have given up
the car?
>> I think Cindy made the right
choice.
>> Yeah.
>> The only thing that I was
thinking about is the fact that
you can give four other people
a car, and it seems like
everyone else was thinking about
what they could have.
So, it kind of made me think
like, am I playing this game too
nicely right now?
Like, should I be playing this
game a little bit harder than I
am?
( bird squawking )
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Hello, everybody.
>> Hello.
>> So, tell me about the
reward, Cindy.
How did it go?
>> It was overwhelming.
We had, you know, some yummy
food, and all the while that
we're cooking and eating, I
could see out of the
corner of my eye that car
sitting there, and to know how
awesome it is and that it's
mine.
>> PROBST: All right, you ready
to get to today's immunity
challenge?
First things first, give it up,
Danni.
>> Oh, gosh.
>> Looks good on you.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
each going to begin attached to
one long piece of rope, which is
wound around a series of poles.
Your goal is to unwind enough
rope to reach the finish line.
In addition, your hands and your
feet will be shackled.
On my "go," you'll reach for ten
keys.
Use one of the keys to unlock
your hands.
Once your hands are free, you'll
move on to the next pole where
you'll unlock your rope and
unwind it from that pole.
When you reach the last lock,
you will also release one final
key.
That will unshackle your feet.
If you think you've untangled
enough rope, sprint to your
flag pole.
First person to the finish to
release their tribe flag wins
immunity-- guaranteed a spot
in the final four.
Clear?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: We'll draw first
spots, and we'll get started.
Here we go.
For immunity and a guaranteed
spot in the final four,
survivors ready?
Go!
First thing you have to do is
unlock your hands.
There are ten keys, not all of
them work.
Steph finds her key very
quickly.
Off to a lead.
Rafe right behind.
Working on their second locks.
Steph and Rafe.
Cindy, Danni, Lydia, still
searching for that first key
to get their hands free.
Cindy's now free.
She's working on her second
lock.
Danni and Lydia still not free.
Steph has her second lock
undone.
Cindy has her second lock
Now begins the unwinding of the
rope.
Hopping over rope, crawling
through and around a pole.
Cindy hopping around.
It's Cindy and Steph in the
lead.
Rafe still working on his second
lock.
Lydia has her hands free.
She's at her second lock.
Danni has her hands free.
Everybody's free.
Steph with a bit of a lead.
Cindy trying to catch up.
Rafe trying to get in it.
Steph working on her third lock.
Cindy moving slowly with those
legs shackled.
Rafe trying to catch up.
Danni and Lydia still behind.
Steph on her third lock.
Cindy now working on her third
lock.
It's Steph and Cindy.
Rafe trying to get enough slack
to get his feet over and not
fall over.
Lydia has her second lock
undone.
She's back in it.
Lydia moving quickly through
these ropes.
Steph still working on her third
lock.
Lydia is now at her third lock.
Cindy at her third lock.
Rafe now at his third lock.
Danni has her second lock
undone.
Steph's been at her lock for a
long time, trying key after key.
Everybody's still in it.
Who's going to find the key
first?
Steph has her lock undone.
Steph now moving towards her
fourth and final lock.
Cindy has her third lock undone.
She's in it.
Steph working on her fourth and
final lock.
Rafe's in it.
He's got his third lock undone.
Steph has her final lock undone.
She has the final key.
She's got to unshackle her feet.
Steph, very close.
Cindy not giving up.
Steph, unshackles her feet,
Cindy racing, Rafe's back in it.
Steph getting as much rope as
she can, taking off to the
finish.
Got to reach the flag and
release it.
Will she have enough?
Steph just short.
She's got a knot, trying to undo
it.
Cindy in her final lock.
If she can get it open in time,
she's got a shot.
Steph did not have enough rope.
Still doesn't have enough rope.
She's got another knot to undo.
Cindy fighting to get back in
this.
Steph within a couple of feet.
Will she have enough rope?
Guaranteed spot in the final
four if she does.
Cindy is at her final lock,
can't get it open.
Steph releases the last knot.
Will this be enough?
Steph wins immunity!
Guaranteed spot in the final
four!
>> Oh, my God, finally I won
something!
>> PROBST: Is this your first
individual win?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Steph, you've come a
long way from day one when you
weren't sure you'd make it
through the first Tribal
Council.
With this, you're guaranteed a
spot in the final four.
>> Good job, Stephenie.
>> PROBST: Rafe, Cindy, Danni,
Lydia, 36 long days about to
come to an end for one of you
tonight.
Tribal Council should be a very
interesting afternoon.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp, I'll see you at Tribal.
♪ ♪
>> Way to go, Steph.
Your family is going to be so
proud of you.
( indistinct chatter )
Day 36.
Mark it on your torch.
>> I know.
>> 36.
>> Cindy, you were right behind
me, right?
>> Didn't get the right key.
>> I finally won individual
immunity.
It's the most amazing feeling,
like, ever.
I just guaranteed myself a spot
in the final four, and I did
not think I was going to get
past the first Tribal Council in
the game.
>> I really feel like I can
trust Rafe.
He said that he wouldn't vote
for me.
I don't know, you can't really
trust anybody out here, but he
seems to be a pretty honest guy,
so hopefully I'll be okay
tonight.
If I somehow win immunity or
something happens, I will.
>> Danni promised me she'd take
me to the final two.
That's a huge degree of security
at the end of a crazy, crazy
game.
I think it's definitely possible
that people could want to get
rid of Danni at this point, but
nothing could really change my
mind about voting out Cindy.
You know, the reward challenge
was the first thing where I
stepped back and was, like,
whoa.
Maybe I'm not going to be
Cindy's biggest fan.
It will come down to my powers
of persuasion here, but I'm
pretty sure that I can convince
Steph we should vote out Cindy.
>> You do?
>> For sure.
You know what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, but now if I vote off
Cindy, there's another vote,
I'm not going to get Jamie's,
Judd's or Cindy's, if I get the
two.
>> Wait. Did you make a deal
with Cindy?
>> No.
I mean, I told her that I was
pretty sure that we were
sticking together, me and you
and her.
It seems like Rafe is leaning
towards getting rid of Cindy,
and I told him I felt
really bad because we already
turned on Judd, and Cindy is in
our alliance, and now we're
going to be turning on Cindy,
and now I don't know if this is
gonna make me look worse,
because Cindy just took me on
a reward, and this might be
another vote I could lose when
it comes time for the jury.
But the same time, she's a huge
threat in this game, and she
knows it, and she has a car at
least.
So, I don't know what's going to
happen. I don't know.
Earlier today, I was, like...
talking about, Danni, right?
And he's like, "I was," but
he's like, " We kind of think
that Cindy is a bigger threat
because he'd rather go up
against Danni.
For some reason, they think
like you're this huge threat.
Right, well he knows that,
but....
>> When I was on the reward
Stephenie, we talked about
eliminating Danni, but now I
know Rafe is more of a threat
than anyone, so if I could get
rid of Rafe, I think that would
be to my benefit.
I think the girls were having a
much better shot at, you know,
winning this.
Danni, just so you know, voting
me out tonight, you're keeping
in your strongest competitor
right there.
He's going to beat you guys in
all the challenges.
I know you guys think I'm a
threat because I've won a couple
of them, but he's just going to
beat you guys in the challenges
and then vote you out.
>> I know he's the strongest.
>> He can beat any of us in the
immunity.
We already know that.
>> Yeah.
There's nothing he can't do.
Smartest thing would be to
eliminate him.
Have all girls go to the final
four.
>> PROBST: I'll now bring in the
members of our jury.
Bobby John, Jamie, Gary and
Judd, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Okay, it's day 36.
There are five of you left.
Steph's going to be one of the
final four.
One other person is going home
tonight.
Rafe, what was the mood like at
camp this afternoon?
>> I think everyone's feeling
threatened right now.
Except Steph, who has the
immunity idol, and there's four
guys in a row on the jury, and
I'm the last guy here, so I
certainly was feeling threatened
around camp today, too.
>> PROBST: Danni, what is the
temperature back at camp, in
terms of paranoia, or stick to
whatever plan you have?
>> Well, I felt uneasy since the
merge because, number-wise, I've
always been the odd man out, so
I always feel worried.
I mean, I'm so lucky to be here,
I mean, to be if the final five.
>> PROBST: Cindy, at the reward
challenge, you win the car
reward, and I tell you that in
ten seasons, the person who has
won that reward has never won
the game, and I give you a
chance to give it up and get rid
of that curse, and also gain
favor by giving everybody else a
car.
You say no, I'm keeping it, and
I'm going to win the game.
Still feel confident you can
break that curse, keep that car
and win the million bucks?
>> Well, I don't feel like I
made the wrong decision because
in this game, there's no
guarantees.
They could very likely vote you
out the next day after you gave
them a car, then you're left
with nothing.
So I thought the curse thing was
silly, that if you win the car,
you're not going to win a
million dollars.
The curse is being a strong
competitor and winning thing,
regardless of what it is, a car,
a pile of cookies, whatever it
is.
If you are a tough competitor,
that's your curse.
I don't think it has anything to
do with the car.
So, I'm totally content with the
decision that I made.
I think I made the right one.
>> PROBST: Who here do you think
is-is competitive?
Who else should have a target on
their back?
>> As far as the competition, I
think Rafe is the one that
people should be most concerned
about.
We all have seen him win
challenge after challenge,
whether it's physical or mental,
so he's good at everything, and
people like him.
So, there you go.
That's the complete package.
>> PROBST: Okay, Steph, you have
the immunity necklace, just to
make sure-- you're keeping it?
>> I'm keeping it.
>> PROBST: Okay, Steph is the
only person you cannot vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Cindy, you're up.
>> You're just a tough
competitor in all walks of
competition, and, dang it,
people just like you.
>> What a terrific person you
are, but you're very athletic,
very competitive and very
intelligent, and I'm voting with
the tribe.
>> Cindy, I've always known
you'd vote whichever way the
wind was blowing in a game where
I'm the biggest threat and it's
always blowing towards me.
I have to vote you out.
I love you, though.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Rafe.
Cindy.
One vote Cindy, one vote Rafe.
Two votes Cindy, one vote Rafe.
14th person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala, Cindy.
That's three votes.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> I'll think about you guys
when I see the stars through my
sunroof of my new car.
>> PROBST: Cindy, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
You've made it to the final
four.
Over the next three days, you
will have three Tribal Councils,
two immunity challenges, one
winner.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp. Good night.
( theme song playing )
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
With only three days left....
>> I'm not going to give up.
>> PROBST: Everything is on the
line.
>> I have a chance to win a
million dollars.
>> I'm going to give them hell.
I'm so nervous.
>> PROBST: The 15th person voted
out of Survivor: Guatemala.
Join us for the two-hour finale
and find out who will be the
sole survivor.
>> I think the one thing I'll
miss the most is the sounds of
the jungle.
The cicadas, the birds, the
howler monkeys, the frogs that
literally is nature's orchestra.
So, yeah, I didn't win the
million bucks, but I've got
memories that are priceless.
There are no dollar signs on
things that I'm gonna have in my
head, my heart, as a result of