>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor... Jamie had it out
with Gary.
>> You are calling me a liar,
and I don't like that.
>> I did not just call you a
liar.
>> Well, obviously, me and you
are going to have to fight this
whole thing now.
>> PROBST: The next day, the
tribe learned they would compete
for a night away from camp.
The winning team will leave here
via helicopter to a beautiful
private home.
The tribe was split into two
teams of four.
Survivors ready, go!
Lydia, Cindy, Jamie, and Rafe's
team took an early lead.
Gary and Judd trying to hang on.
But Lydia couldn't keep up.
>> I can't get my feet up.
Steph and Danni surged ahead and
won reward for their team.
( cheering )
Danni, Steph, Gary, Judd win
reward!
Living in luxury, Danni, Steph,
and Gary bonded.
>> Danni and I are, like, really
similar.
She's a cool chick.
>> Two hot girls get in the
shower together.
>> I wouldn't go that far, not
right now.
>> PROBST: And Gary took the
opportunity to make his move.
>> I want to take the strongest
four to the final four.
Because if Lydia goes to the
final two, guess who's winning?
>> We know that.
>> If Cindy goes to the final
two, guess who's winning?
And do they deserve it?
>> Let me ask you this, then.
Numbers aside, who would be the
next person you guys would want
to vote out?
>> Jamie.
>> PROBST: But Judd wasn't
buying into Gary's plea.
>> Bonding with Gary and Danni
is not going to affect my game,
because I know what my game plan
is.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready.
Go!
The race for immunity was tight.
It's Cindy and Rafe right now.
But it was Rafe who came away
with the victory.
Rafe wins immunity.
( applause and cheering )
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: With Tribal Council
looming, Judd reassured Jamie
that Gary was the next to go.
>> Are we good and solid?
>> Mm-hmm.
We're going to vote for Gary
tonight.
Jamie's just very paranoid.
I mean, he's not going anywhere.
>> PROBST: But Lydia, Stephenie,
and Rafe were conspiring against
Jamie behind Judd's back.
>> I know that, but...
Gary is a smooth operator.
>> I think we should do it.
>> I don't know what to say, you
know.
I mean... it's a hard decision.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Judd was surprised to see his
alliance turn on one of its own,
as Jamie was voted out.
Jamie, the tribe has spoken.
>> Blindsided. Nice!
>> PROBST: Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Ooh, crazy, ooh.
>> I'm fine, man, I just, I
don't know what to say, man.
I wish somebody would have told
me, man.
I guess, I don't know.
>> All I want to say is I wanted
to tell you, we all did, but why
even put you in that situation?
>> No, that's fine.
>> Because you're close to
Jamie, and then you were going
to feel super uncomfortable.
>> I'm just confused.
That was it.
I was just shocked, completely,
totally shocked that Jamie got
voted out, man.
We were supposed to have an
alliance of six, and it kind of
went berserk today, and, yeah, I
was pissed off, man.
Don't feel bad for Judd,
'cause Judd doesn't even feel
bad, whatsoever.
I'm telling you.
>> I can tell you're, like, okay
with it.
>> I don't feel bad at all.
>> Here comes the backstabbing
and lying.
It makes me wonder, from now on,
what the hell is going on, man.
>> There's no doubt that I
dodged a bullet tonight.
My old ties in Yaxha at the
beginning of the game helped me
out, but Jamie did me a big
favor by driving everybody
crazy.
>> I just feel already a breath
of fresh air.
>> I just feel like all is right
in Survivor world.
>> It is.
>> For now.
>> Just for a minute.
( chuckling )
( birds singing )
( snoring )
>> Gary was supposed to go home
yesterday, but we had a little
twist, and we did decide to vote
Jamie off.
And I thought about it, you
know, whether I did the right
thing or not, and I don't know
if this alliance is still
strong.
I really have to figure this
out, but I have to do this
carefully, because if I don't,
I'm going to be the next target.
>> I woke up this morning.
I had my head kind of looking
out the lean-to, and I heard
Gary working all over Lydia,
man, like you couldn't believe,
man, just working her.
And Lydia's like, "Oh, yeah,
yeah."
Her eyes are bulging out of her
head.
"Yeah, Gary."
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Rafe.
>> Huh?
>> Come here.
>> What happened?
>> They were just talking, and
Gary's like, "So what do you
think, Lydia?
What do you want to do?"
And Lydia is like, "I don't
know."
>> She's not going to go with
it.
>> I swear to God, dude.
>> I think Judd has changed
since Jamie was voted out,
because Judd's growing insecure
now and wants to find security
with people, and so I think
Steph and I can give him that.
Me, Judd, and Steph are pretty
confident in each other at this
point.
And I think Gary and Danni have
managed to pull over Lydia in a
real way.
>> When we went on our reward,
Gary had told me that he wanted
Cindy and Lydia out of this game
already and they shouldn't even
be here.
Okay, now he wants them in the
game, and he's trying to make an
alliance with them.
So that's a big lie.
He likes to think that he's no
part of this lying game, but the
least person you would expect to
lie is basically the biggest
liar.
I need a tad bit more.
>> What is your strategy here?
>> Okay, okay.
>> I mean, because we got to
have four, so that's why I
wanted to talk to you, because
I'd rather go with you than some
of them.
>> I'm going with you, but the
thing is, the thing is...
you know, I, I wasn't sure about
Cindy.
Stephenie, Judd, Rafe, Cindy,
and myself, we're all in this
together now, final five, but
the thing is I have to cover my
own ass, you know.
I'm going to have to see how far
this game is going to take me.
So if somebody approach me with
a better deal, I'm going with
it.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
How's everybody doing?
>> Good.
>> PROBST: Shall we get to
today's challenge?
Today's challenge is for reward.
Each of you will have three pots
filled with corn.
I'm going to ask you a series of
questions about the Maya culture
and Guatemala.
Each time you answer a question
correctly, you earn the right to
smash another tribe member's pot
of corn.
When all three of your pots are
smashed, you're out of the game.
Last person with a pot left
hanging wins reward.
Do you want to know what you are
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The winner will leave
here and be taken to a true
natural wonder of Guatemala.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: It's a hot springs
waterfall cascading down into a
pool of cool water.
So when combined, they create
this spa-like environment that
is very relaxing.
You'll have mojitos.
( gasping )
You'll have skewered meat,
shrimp, beef, chicken.
You'll also have a massage.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get
started.
First question: the Maya
recorded their stories by
carving hieroglyphics into stone
monuments known as A: Stella, B:
Origami, C: Sanskrit or D: Docky
Rocks.
Everybody reveal.
Steph says C: Sanskrit.
That is wrong.
Correct answer is A: Stella.
Everybody else has it right.
All right, Judd, you're up
first, take your swing.
>> Don't do it, Judd.
>> PROBST: Already, the
negotiating begins.
Judd goes right to Gary.
Nothing subtle about that, Gary.
>> No.
>> Lydia.
>> How did I know?
>> PROBST: Wow.
>> PROBST: Stephenie down a pot.
Danni.
>> Man.
>> PROBST: Stephenie takes her
second hit.
Cindy.
Cindy knocks Gary's second pot
down.
Gary down to one pot.
Stephenie down to one pot.
Rafe moves to Danni, smashes
Danni's first pot.
Gary has two people to pay back.
Gary takes out Cindy.
Next question: in the Maya court
ball game, members of the losing
team were frequently killed.
True or false, often they would
be decapitated and their heads
would then be encased to be used
as the ball in future games.
Everybody reveal.
Steph takes a look down to see
what other people are doing.
Makes her choice, and she makes
the wrong choice.
It is true.
Lydia has it right.
Danni has it right.
Cindy has it right.
That's it.
Lydia, take your whack.
Lydia could put somebody out of
this game... and she does.
Steph the first casualty.
>> Jealousy gets you nowhere.
>> I'm hungry. I want to eat.
>> We'll see about that.
>> PROBST: Steph not happy at
all with that, Lydia.
>> I haven't eaten.
Steph ate three times.
>> So did Gary, so did Danni.
>> PROBST: Game's getting
interesting.
Danni, take your shot.
Judd takes his first hit.
Cindy, what's she going to do?
Boy, she's winding up.
Wow.
Cindy takes Gary out of the
game.
Gary not happy.
Just like that, we're down to
five.
Next question, the ancient Maya
believed that the gods fashioned
man from which spiritually
important crop, A: Coffee, B:
Cocoa Beans, C: Corn, or D:
Ramon Nuts.
Judd trying to see any clue of
what to put down.
Everybody reveal.
Judd says, B: Cocoa Beans.
No, the correct answer was C:
Corn.
Everybody else has it right.
Judd takes his second hit.
Danni could put Judd out of
this, and she does.
Judd takes a seat on the bench.
Cindy heading down to the end.
Danni now down to one pot.
Rafe could take her out, and he
does.
>> Come join the loser's lounge.
>> PROBST: Danni takes a seat on
the bench.
We are now down to three.
Lydia has all three pots left.
Rafe has all three pots left.
Cindy has two pots left.
Which of the following countries
does not border Guatemala, A: is
Belize, B: Honduras, C: Costa
Rica, D: El Salvador.
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer, Rafe has it, C:
Costa Rica.
Take your shot.
Rafe breaks Lydia's first pot.
Lydia and Cindy down to two
pots.
Rafe still has all three.
True or false: the temples of
Tikal are the only ancient Maya
structures to be built during
the Maya Empire with the aid of
modern machinery.
Reveal.
Everybody says false.
I'm so glad everybody got it
right.
There was no modern machinery in
ancient Maya.
Cindy, you're up.
Big decision now.
Does Rafe get his first hit, or
does Lydia take her second?
Cindy knocks Lydia's second pot
out.
And with that, Lydia is out of
the game.
But, Lydia, because you got it
right, you get your last licks.
Two people to pay back, only one
swing to do it with.
Lydia is done.
Does her damage, takes a seat on
the bench.
We are now down to two.
Big reward at stake.
Both of you have two pots left.
True or false: there are 30
volcanoes here in Guatemala.
Reveal.
Rafe says false, Cindy says
true.
Correct answer is...
Cindy got it right.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Just like that, Rafe
is down to one pot.
If Cindy gets it right,
regardless what you do, Cindy
wins.
True or false: the most active
time of day for crocodiles is at
dawn.
Reveal.
Rafe says true.
Cindy says false.
Crocodiles are most active not
at dawn, but at dusk.
The answer is false.
>> Cindy!
Whoo!
>> PROBST: So here is the deal.
You are going to leave here, go
to a beautiful place.
Got some food, got some drink,
got a massage.
You got one person going with
you.
( groans )
>> This is the most difficult
decision of the whole game.
Judd's sitting over there
praying.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Pick one.
>> I'll go with Rafe.
>> PROBST: Rafe is going.
Cindy and Rafe, heading off to a
great reward.
Steph, Judd, Lydia, Danni, Gary,
head on back to camp.
>> We get to the challenge, and,
lo and behold, I'm the first
one out.
Lydia hits me twice.
Danni hits me once.
Knocked me right out.
Lydia was fed up because I've
won so many food rewards, and
she's starving out here.
Well, boo-hoo for Lydia.
I'm sick of hearing your crap.
You're lucky you're still in the
game.
I just want to say, just to get
it out there, I had burgers,
burgers, burgers.
Feast, feast, you had pizza, you
had pasta.
>> The only one that didn't eat
here was Lydia.
>> We've all had three, and then
I chose, personally, not to
compete in the immunity
challenge.
I put my ass on the line, and I
ate, so I had one extra, and
that was not a reward.
'Cause everybody is talking,
"Stephenie's eating so much.
I'm so upset Stephenie is
winning all these rewards."
>> I wasn't...
>> And I don't want to hear
anymore about it.
There's a winner and a loser in
this game, and if you're gonna
be jealous, then you're an
idiot.
I made that clear as soon as I
got back to camp.
I shut everybody up right then
and there.
You think that a challenge like
this isn't going to show me
where your loyalties lie, you
are sadly mistaken.
I've had three, you've had
three, you've had three, you've
had three.
We're all pretty even.
>> Which I don't care, one way
or the other.
But a pizza compared to what you
ate was nothing.
Lydia was very upset because
Steph eats a stinking ton.
I don't think she's lost weight.
She eats so much corn and nuts
it's amazing.
So I know she is strong.
And she needs to be looked at at
these challenges, 'cause she can
win.
>> I'm not going to take
anything personal, I'm not, but
when I hear people saying that
I've eaten too much and that
they're starving and that I get
all the rewards, I just want to
set the record straight that
we're pretty damn even now.
>> This wasn't personal.
If I won, I was going to take
Rafe, because I felt Rafe and I
were the only two that hadn't
had a meal, and that was the
only reason why.
>> Everything in this game is
personal, man.
I mean, I hear people, I see
people every day lying through
their damn teeth who I least
expect to lie, so when you say
nothing is personal, everything
is personal, man.
>> Stephenie was the first one
out, and I think she was pretty
upset.
I wanted to give somebody else a
chance for the food reward that
hadn't had a chance, you know?
Right now, everybody is putting
Stephenie up on a pedestal.
Everybody is knowing that
Stephenie is the biggest threat,
but nobody is doing anything
about it.
>> Well, I'm glad that's over,
and if you think I'm eating too
much or getting too many
rewards, just tell me next time,
because I'm going to hear about
it.
>> This is amazing.
>> Hola.
>> Oh, my gosh, it's beautiful.
>> I'm just, like, completely
ecstatic that I actually won a
reward, a really cool reward.
And I couldn't have picked a
better person to share it with.
>> Oh, gracias.
>> There was this gorgeous
waterfall and then a huge
platter of shishkabobs and
mojito pitchers and then a
massage table.
We were like, "Do we eat first?
Do we get massages?
What do we do?"
And, of course, we decided to
eat first, because, I mean, we
had to.
To the first of many feasts
and exotic locations together.
>> Cheers.
>> We have to eat all of this.
>> Look, watermelon.
Oh, this is so freakin' good.
>> I just can't believe we're
eating.
>> So, back at camp, Lydia is
probably really irritated that
she's not eating.
Gary is mad because I took him
out.
Stephenie and Judd are probably
sitting up on the ruins laughing
at it all.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Lydia is so easily swayed.
>> Spending too much time with
Gary, getting brainwashed.
>> It was kind of like a flood
of strategy out of both of us.
After that, it was like, you
know, Cindy and I are kind of in
this together for better or
for worse.
>> Oh, you can feel the warm
water-- come on.
The water coming down out of the
waterfall was hot, not warm, hot
like taking-a-shower hot.
And then the water down
underneath was cold, and it was
crystal clear.
It was one of the coolest things
you could possibly see.
>> We went into the waterfall
together.
You know, I was holding her and
helping her move.
And I am a really touchy person,
and Cindy is not, so it was nice
to kind of be able to, like,
feel that touchy-feely kind of
connection with Cindy.
>> It feels really, really good,
like every muscle in my entire
body is loose and relaxed.
I've not been that relaxed in,
you know, over a month.
And it was icing on the cake.
That was awesome, huh?
>> This was, like, the best day
ever.
It was just such an amazing
experience to be in the
waterfall, and to have the food,
and to have the massage.
>> I'm so relaxed I can't even
get my shoes on my feet.
>> Mm-hmm.
That reward was just like, I can
make it, for the rest of this
game.
We can do this.
>> Aren't you thirsty?
>> Yeah.
>> This makes me thirsty.
>> I'm always thirsty.
>> Lydia, can you bring that
pitcher over?
>> Yeah.
>> Are you done with that cup?
>> Yeah, clean cup, too.
>> Thank you.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Hi!
>> Hi, guys!
How was the feast?
>> It was like a plate of
shishkabobs.
It wasn't a ton of food.
Like, we just ate quickly and
then, like, went down and kind
of showered off in the
waterfall.
We came back to camp after the
reward challenge, and I was
like, "Uh-oh, who's going to
make us feel comfortable about
what happened?"
>> Tell us from the beginning,
like, when you got there.
>> As soon as you got there,
with the platter waiting for
you.
>> There was shrimp and
vegetables, and then steak and
vegetables.
>> The shrimp was best.
But it was really nice.
It definitely was relaxing.
>> Good, I'm so glad you guys
got to do that.
>> Cindy and Rafe came back to
camp and they shared the
experience with everybody.
I had to listen to them, you
know, about how good the food
was and the shishkabob, and the
mojitos, and what have you.
I felt insulted.
Cindy should have chosen me to
go to this food reward.
I'm an outcast.
That's what I feel like.
>> Oh.
>> Try it?
>> No, no, I've had enough food
today.
>> Okay, okay.
>> Is it good, though?
Did you put coffee in it?
>> No just water, salt, and the
leftovers that nobody wanted.
>> Oh.
>> I didn't want to throw it
away.
>> Lydia had, like, some kind of
corn soup or something in a
little coffee cup eating it
like, you know, she was just
literally dying and she was
scrounging for whatever she
could find to eat.
And it's almost like, you know,
we're supposed to feel sorry for
you, and let you win something.
But, I mean, we're here to
compete, and we're talking final
four, and you've got to step it
up, or you're not going to be
around.
>> We need to stick together, us
four.
>> I think so, too.
>> Because she's nice and
smiles.
>> This next couple of days are
going to be crucial for Lydia,
'cause it could mean that she
goes really far in this game or
is one of the next people to go.
( snoring )
>> One, two...
>> Any of you making coffee?
>> I am right now.
>> The first couple of hours are
one of the better parts of the
day.
We sit around and talk and have
coffee and breakfast.
>> Here she comes.
>> The coffee queen.
>> Stephenie and myself, Judd
and Rafe all had our coffee.
We're up on the ruins, and we
were like, "How cool would it be
if this is the way we spend our
last days?"
>> This corn cake is made all
right?
>> Oh, man.
>> I don't know why.
It just seems like every
morning, my coffee gets better.
>> There's definitely a foursome
that seems to feel they have the
most power.
I would rather be in the power
class right now, but I'm not.
>> The people I totally feel
comfortable with are you and
Rafe.
>> There's three outsiders.
I mean, that's Gary, myself, and
now Lydia, but we need to bring
in a fourth person.
So we're going to try to talk to
Rafe and see what plan of action
we can take.
Hopefully, it'll work out.
Otherwise, I've got to look at
who is control of the game and
play up to it.
You just have to keep trying
until you find something that
works, 'cause I'm not going to
go home.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Come on in, have a seat.
All right, first things first.
Rafe, hand over the immunity
necklace.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
Today, I'm going to tell you a
story about Maya folklore.
You're then gonna race to a
series of seven stations.
You'll find a puzzle.
Put the puzzle together to
reveal a question about the
story.
Read it and choose between one
of two answers.
If you are right, you'll find
colored flags.
Grab yours, bring it back to
your starting platform, and hang
it up.
If you're wrong, you will find
colored sticks.
You must grab your stick, throw
it in the fire before you can go
back to that station or any
other station.
The first person to have all
seven flags hanging from their
starting platform wins immunity.
You ready for the story?
One of the most popular figures
in Mayan mythology is the moon
goddess, Ixchel.
She was also the inventor of
weaving.
Ixchel was married to Itzamna.
He was the creator of the entire
Maya culture.
Together, they had four sons.
They were responsible for
holding up the four corners of
the sky, but that marriage
ended, Ixchel married again.
This time she married the earth
god, Voltan.
Voltan was a human hero, who had
been turned into a god.
But after a short while, Ixchel
grew tired of that and began
having an affair with the sun
god.
This frustrated her grandfather.
He threw lightning down on her,
killing her.
But dragonflies sang over her
body.
She came back to life, went
right back to the affair she was
having with the sun.
This lasted just a few days, and
she began having another affair
with the sun's brother, the
morning star.
This devastated the sun god.
He banished her from his sight
forever.
Today, Ixchel spends her nights
alone in the sky, nursing the
women of earth through their
pregnancy.
As for the sun, when the sun is
in sight, the moon stays hidden.
That's the story.
We'll draw for spots, and we'll
get started.
Here we go, guys.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You get it right, you'll find a
colored flag.
>> PROBST: Lydia racing back
with her first flag.
Lydia first on the board.
>> "Why did Ixchel's grandfather
kill her?"
Because she had an affair.
>> PROBST: Gary back with his
first flag.
>> "Ixchel had four children who
were responsible for holding up
the four corners of the sky.
Who was their father?"
"The creator of the Mayan
culture."
>> PROBST: Danni and Rafe racing
back with their flags.
>> "A human?"
"An animal?"
Um, a human.
>> PROBST: This is for immunity.
Let's go.
Cindy back with her first flag.
>> "Ixchel was goddess of...
>> PROBST: Judd misses his
question.
Got to throw the stick in the
fire before you can go back.
>> Ixchel... is hidden away?
"Throws jugs of water to cause
floods and rain storms."
>> PROBST: Stephenie misses her
first question.
Stephenie and Judd the only two
people not on the board.
Lydia answers incorrectly.
Rafe has his second flag racing
back.
Rafe now in the lead.
Gary right behind.
It's Gary and Rafe, each with
two flags.
Where have I been?
Where haven't I been?
Confusion starting to set in
already.
Cindy back with her second flag.
Lydia with a second flag.
Steph finally on the board.
Judd finally on the board.
>> Ixchel was the inventor of...
weaving.
>> He was a human.
>> PROBST: Rafe back with his
third flag.
Gary back with his third flag.
You need seven flags to win.
30 days out here.
Don't want it to end tonight.
Cindy is in it with three flags.
Lydia wrong again.
>> Because she had an affair?
Because she married Voltan--
( grunts )
>> PROBST: Gary back with his
fourth flag.
Gary now in the lead.
Cindy back with another flag.
Gary and Cindy both have four
flags.
Rafe back with his fourth flag.
We have three people now with
four flags.
Steph with her third flag.
Gary back with his fifth flag.
Gary has not missed a question
yet.
Danni answers wrong.
Rafe back with his fifth flag.
It's Gary and Rafe with five.
Only two flags left.
Cindy with her fifth flag.
Gary, Rafe, Cindy fighting for
immunity.
>> "A human."
>> Ixchel was the goddess of the
moon.
>> PROBST: Here comes Gary with
his sixth flag.
Rafe with his sixth flag.
Rafe and Gary both have one flag
left.
Both have to go to far corners
of the court.
They're still neck and neck.
Gary and Rafe, immunity on the
line.
>> "... corners of the sky-- who
was the further?"
>> ...morning star-- true.
>> PROBST: Gary and Rafe both
heading back with their last
flag.
It's going to be a race.
Rafe back with his seventh flag.
Once again, Rafe wins immunity!
Rafe, come on over.
Once again, you are safe at
Tribal Council tonight.
( applause )
Sadly, everybody else fair game.
One of you will be going home
tonight.
See you guys at Tribal.
Head on back.
>> Good job, everybody.
>> Rafe kicked butt.
>> For the third time, I won
individual immunity.
Who would see this little gay
Mormon and think that he was
going to win most of the
immunity challenges?
It feels really good, because
growing up, I never saw someone
who looked and acted gay and was
also athletic and could... had
confidence in themselves and
could do well in competitions
like this.
>> So far, we got a great
alliance.
>> Such a good alliance, and we
all trust each other.
It's just too funny, because
it's two guys, two girls.
How fair is that?
We started together, you started
together.
>> I mean, it's just like...
>> It's perfect.
It seems too good to be true.
We have such a great alliance,
and we have such trust in one
another that it almost seems too
easy to get to the final four
together.
It feels weird because, last
time, I felt so powerless and
this time I feel so powerful.
It's like a dream almost come
true, but it almost seems too
good to be true.
>> I thought to myself, "I was
loyal to you.
"I was right there with
everything that you wanted me to
"do.
And now, all of a sudden, you
guys don't need me anymore," so
I think I'm screwed.
>> Right now, I think I'm a big
enough threat that they are
going to keep Lydia and Danni
around instead of me.
I'm dealing with some smart
people and people that don't
want me around.
Cindy, obviously, doesn't like
me, so I don't care what happens
to her.
But I'm not going to dwell on
it.
I'm going to just attack the
next avenue and see if I can
just stay in a couple more days.
>> Good, good.
>> Rafe told me that he didn't
trust Judd.
That threw up a red flag.
So at some point they're going
to turn on each other.
The quicker I can make that
happen, the better.
Because if I want to get further
in this game, I'm going to have
to shake things up.
( thunder rumbling )
>> That's like a Jersey storm.
>> At this point of the game, I
don't trust anybody.
You never know who's going to
turn on who, and everybody's
kind of scouring all over the
place.
( thunder rumbling )
>> Whoa-- seriously.
>> Lydia is lost.
I mean, she's just totally lost.
She can't be trusted, so she's
got to go.
And Gary has been running around
here like a damn lunatic, trying
to get anybody on his damn side.
And I don't know if it worked or
not.
You just never know until you
get to Tribal.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury.
Bobby Jon and Jamie voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
Lydia, at the reward challenge,
a lot of hostility between you
and Steph about how much food
was eaten, who's had the most.
You based your cracking of the
pots on that fact entirely.
>> I had a feeling that perhaps
Stephenie might win this one
again, so I said, "Heck with
that."
Nothing personal, but this time
I want to eat.
>> PROBST: Nothing personal?
It's very personal!
>> Well, Stephenie is also very
liked in this tribe, and
whenever anybody wins food
reward challenge, they invite
her.
But when we came back to camp,
Stephenie made it very clear to
me, "Hey, you know, enough of
this, enough of this stuff about
me eating, you know.
I want it to stop right there."
And I looked at her and I said,
"You know, hey, this is a game
Steph.
"You know, nothing personal, but
I just wanted a chance to eat."
>> PROBST: Who is running the
camp right now?
>> Well, everybody looks up to
Stephenie.
She's played the game before, so
in my eyes, it seems as if Steph
is running the show.
>> PROBST: Steph, that is really
just driving you bonkers
listening to that.
>> I'm definitely not running
the show.
Did I say I wanted it to stop
when I we came back?
You're damn right.
I said, "Listen, if you got
something to say, say it to my
face.
"If not, I don't want to hear it
anymore."
That's all I said.
So if that's running the show...
>> PROBST: Gary, what's your
take on this?
>> I personally like Steph, but
there's some people here that
are star-struck by her.
That's not her fault, but they
all can probably get her
autograph after the show.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Cindy, are you happy
with how you've played the game?
Ethically.
No compromises. I'm good.
>> Yep, mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: Judd, happy with how
you played?
>> Absolutely. Definitely.
>> PROBST: But in terms of
ethics-- whether or not to lie--
did you come into this with any
sort of moral compass, or is it,
"Hey, it's Survivor, are you
nuts?"
>> To be honest with you, I
don't think I've lied yet, but I
think I'm going to start lying,
though.
Everybody here is lying about
everything.
I mean, for the last past couple
of days, there's been lies, man,
over here, over there, up there,
over here.
That's basically what's going
on, man.
I mean, everybody is sitting
here like things are fine and
dandy, but that ain't the case,
man, seriously.
So if I want to stick around in
this game, I'd better start
lying.
And you know what?
I'm a damn bad liar, so I might
be in trouble, man.
>> PROBST: You said there were
lies all over the place.
What are you referring to?
>> When we went on that reward,
it was me, Danni, Gary, and
Steph.
Gary came flat out and said,
"Cindy and Lydia should not even
be here.
"They were riding coattail the
whole damn way, and they have
no damn reason to even be in
this game."
That came right out of his
mouth.
>> That's right, and so what did
I lie about?
>> Because then you're trying to
make an alliance with Lydia.
>> But I didn't say...
>> You wanted her out of the
game.
>> But did I tell them that they
should be out of the game?
I didn't tell them that.
>> You told me that.
>> I know, but that's not a lie.
>> Oh, that's a lie.
>> That's playing the game.
How is that a lie?
>> I know, that's playing the
game.
>> But that's not a lie.
I didn't lie to them.
This is a lie.
"Hey, you guys the idol is on
the ground."
That's a lie.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Gary, what's the
comment you're talking about the
idol is on the ground?
>> Way back when he got the clue
about the idol, he goes, "Okay,
I'll tell you, it's on the
ground."
Well, I followed him out in the
woods the next day, and he is
looking at all the trees.
So I said, "Hmm, that's strange.
He told me it was on the
ground."
So I made myself seen in the
woods, and all of a sudden, he
starts throwing rocks around,
and the idol was in the tree.
>> PROBST: Okay, Judd, you got
caught.
You got outed tonight for lying.
>> Okay, all right, I lied about
the damn idol.
Okay.
I told you I'm a bad liar.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Rafe, you have the immunity
necklace.
I can't imagine you are giving
it up.
>> I want to keep it.
>> PROBST: Rafe is the only one
you cannot vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Lydia, you're up.
>> Gary, you've been running
around the jungle for two days,
man, like a squirrel trying to
get a damn nut, man.
Do me a favor and get the hell
out of here.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Gary.
Cindy.
One vote Gary, one vote Cindy.
Gary.
Two votes Gary, one vote Cindy.
That's three votes Gary.
12th person voted out
of Survivor: Guatemala, Gary.
That's four, it's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Gary, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, one thing is becoming
clear to me from these Tribal
Councils, and that is nobody is
going down without a fight.
Which means over the next nine
days, there should be some big
battles.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, Danni feels the
pressure.
>> This perfect little alliance
is going to have to start
breaking up.
I'm definitely not going to go
down without a fight.
>> PROBST: Lydia makes a move.
>> How far do you want to get to
the final two?
>> Just as far as you do.
>> We have seven freakin' days
left.
Maybe it's time we make a
difference.
>> PROBST: And the tribe is
shocked.
>> This is so random!
>> What a great time. I had fun.
It was great competition.
Loved meeting the people.
My tribe does not know my real
name, which is Gary Hogeboom.
I didn't feel that it would be
an advantage if they knew that I
used to play in the NFL.
So that was the lie I told, but
I told it because I wanted to be
judged on how I played the game,