>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor... Yaxha dodged deadly
visitors.
>> Wow.
>> It ate something.
That could have been one of us
if we were swimming across its
path.
>> What?
>> A fish got me.
>> PROBST: Then everything
changed when the tribes were
unexpectedly switched.
Drop your buffs.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Danni, Brandon,
Bobby Jon and Blake were the new
members of Yaxha, and Jamie,
Lydia, Rafe and Stephenie
joined Nakum.
At the new Nakum tribe,
Stephenie and Jamie approached
Judd about turning on his old
tribe mate Brooke.
>> Then we'll get rid of Brooke.
>> Like I said, man, I'm all
with you guys, man.
I'm all for that, man.
>> PROBST: And Margaret felt
uneasy about Judd's loyalties.
>> With this switch-up today, I
don't feel safe at all.
>> I know I'm the big gun around
here.
You feel like you're King Kong,
man.
( deep, raspy hooting )
>> PROBST: At Yaxha, Brian, Amy
and Gary felt the pressure of
being outnumbered by their new
tribe mates, three to four.
>> We're decimated here.
>> PROBST: Blake and Bobby Jon
shared a private moment to
confirm their game plan.
>> Bobby and I, you know, had a
little bathroom break and a
little pep talk.
We already picked the order.
It's Amy, Brian and Gary out the
door.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
>> Come on, Brian, keep on
popping them, Brandon.
>> PROBST: Yaxha threw their way
to victory.
Yaxha wins immunity!
Back at Nakum, Margaret
pressured Judd to vote off Lydia
and keep the four former Nakum
members united.
>> They're going to be four,
we'll be three.
They can pick us off one by one.
>> PROBST: And Judd doubted his
new alliance.
>> My biggest concern right now,
of course, is Jamie and
Stephenie not being as loyal as
they say they are.
So, when I go to Tribal Council,
I don't know who I'm going to
choose.
>> PROBST: But in the end, Judd
turned his back on his former
tribe mates and helped vote out
Brooke.
Brooke, the tribe has spoken.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> God, I'm, like, so friggin'
sick of Tribal Coun...
Like, I don't ever even want to
go there ever again.
>> At Tribal Council, Brooke got
voted out.
It was me who went the opposite
of what my tribe went.
You know, I'm feeling good about
it.
It's every man for himself out
here.
You know, you do have to
remember that it is a cutthroat
game, so...
>> And you're absolutely right,
Judd.
>> So, I mean, you can't throw
everybody on an island and play
this game.
It's a tough game, man.
>> It absolutely is.
>> We're all here to play a game
and we're all here to win a
million dollars.
>> Right.
>> And whichever way we do it
and how we do it is up to us.
>> I'm just really sad at what
Judd has done.
Judd flipped the very first day
the new tribe came to be, and he
didn't bother to look back.
He's a traitor.
>> Now that is an inappropriate
statement.
>> I mean, because they're not
in my shoes and they're not
playing the game I'm playing.
It's a tough game, man.
As long as my wife and my
daughter and my family love me,
that's all that matters to me,
baby.
The only thing that matters to
me.
I want to see how it plays out.
I hope my alliance stays the way
it is.
Margaret, she's probably not too
happy with it, but I really
don't care whether she's happy
or not.
I can't wait until she goes,
too.
>> This morning I'm sitting here
thinking about, you know, how am
I sitting in this game right now
and what chances do I have at
this point?
I think I've got a pretty good
chance.
The group I have over here, with
Yaxha, there's seven of us and
four of us from the original
Nakum: Bobby Jon, Brandon, Danni
and I.
I don't think it could have
worked out better.
We came over here with the new
Yaxha tribe.
We have the odds.
Gary and Brian and Amy are
amazing, but they've got to know
they got a target on their back
if we lose.
So I'm liking my odds right now.
>> Aah! What is that?
>> It's a beetle.
>> Get it out of here.
Get it the ... out of here!
I don't want it near me.
>> It's chasing you.
>> Whoa, it landed right on your
shoulder.
>> Get it off, get it off!
>> I'm just joking with you.
>> I didn't know beetles could
fly.
>> They're magical beetles here.
>> It sounded like a helicopter.
I was like, what is that?
>> Amy, she lived her whole life
in the city.
She said she's never been
camping or anything.
I don't know. I'm from Kansas.
The great state of Kansas.
And I don't know, I'm used to
more farming type of people--
maybe the rednecks, the hicks,
you know, that kind of people.
>> What do you farm?
>> Wheat, milo, soybeans.
>> So then, when you go and it's
done, you go and pull it out?
With my new Yaxha tribe, a lot
of people are constantly talking
about farm stuff.
I have no idea.
Wheat, what do you do with it?
>> Wheat?
Wheat's used for bread...
>> No, I know what it's used
for, but how do you...
Tell me about the process.
>> If you go out there and get a
planter and you put a bunch of
seed in your planter...
>> I'm like from the city, so,
when they talk about farming and
stuff, I definitely am the odd
man out.
>> You got little plows in front
of it and you got seed bins in
the back.
>> We prefer John Deere.
>> John Deere.
>> Most of these people I
probably wouldn't be friends
with outside of the game.
They come from different parts
of the country, you know.
I'm very New England, I'm very
blue state, and they're very
Texas and, you know, they're
from Tulsa, Oklahoma, or...
it's just not my style.
>> Wow.
You know, they're good people,
so I don't dislike them at all.
But they're just not the kind of
people I'm used to hanging out
with.
>> Dear Heavenly Father, in
Jesus' name, Lord, we thank You
for this day, thank You for
every day out here, Lord.
>> Our tribe is a very religious
tribe.
We say grace before every meal.
We pray before every challenge.
We thank Jesus for everything.
You know, and I'm not a
religious person at all.
But I'm not going to object to
it, that would be stupid.
You'd be stupid to say, like,
you know what, guys?
I don't want to thank Jesus for
this meal, thanks.
Because then they'd vote me
right out-- that's dumb.
Even if I object to something,
you have to grin and bear it.
That's the strategy out here.
>> Amen.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Yaxha, come on in.
Nakum, come on in.
Yaxha, getting your first look
at the new Nakum tribe.
Brooke voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Tell me about life at Nakum.
Steph, what's the water
situation?
>> We can't go in the water.
The water is very muddy and
murky, so we just dump the
bucket over our heads to try to
stay cool.
>> PROBST: It's been over 100
degrees every single day we've
been out here.
The only relief you have is that
water.
>> It's miserable heat out here,
Jeff.
I mean, it sucks life out of
you.
Not to be able to just dive in
and swim around in that pretty
green water is a bummer.
We float in, we sit in waist
deep and splash water on
ourselves and just kind of enjoy
the beach.
>> There was a croc five feet
from our dock, so I'm always
like bitching for them to get
back in.
>> PROBST: Wait, this is news to
me. You've seen a croc?
>> I saw one this morning.
>> PROBST: You saw one this
morning?
>> I got up this morning to
watch the sunrise and one swam
right on the shoreline.
He came out.
I just watched the five, six-
foot crocodile swim out to the
big part of the lake.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to today's challenge.
It is for reward.
Here's how it works.
On my go, both tribes will race
to the first station where one
tribe member will cut through a
rope using a sharp stone, just
like the ancient Maya would
have.
Once you cut through the rope,
you'll release two hammers.
Untie them, take them with you
to the second station where
a different tribe member will
chop through a log to a second
rope.
Once you've chopped through the
log and the rope, you'll release
two more handles.
You now have four handles.
Take those with you, race up the
platform, where four different
tribe members will take the
handles and put them in a
turnstile and begin cranking it.
As you crank that turnstile, you
will bring a cart up the hill,
closer and closer toward you.
Once that cart reaches the top,
all six tribe members who have
participated thus far get in the
cart.
That leaves one tribe member
left.
Their sole responsibility, take
a machete, chop the final rope;
that will release the cart and
send it screaming down the hill.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: First tribe to the
finish wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes, sir!
>> PROBST: Very few things can
take the edge off of an
unbearably hot day.
This is certainly one of them.
For the winners, margaritas,
chip and dip with guacamole.
Granted, it would be nice if you
could go back to a refreshing
body of water, as if there
weren't crocs-- make it a little
better, wouldn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Second part of the
reward for the winning tribe, a
floating, crocodile-proof swim
cage.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Delivered to your
camp, complete with decking,
lounge chairs and an umbrella.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Just for today?
>> PROBST: Stays at your camp.
Give you a minute to strategize
and we'll get started.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Let Jamie go.
>> PROBST: Strategy critical in
this.
Jamie and Brandon getting to
work on the rope using the
stones.
>> Go, Jamie!
>> PROBST: Brandon kind of
hacking at it.
He's through the first rope very
quickly.
Brandon's got a strategy, using
some leverage.
Jamie's still working on that
first rope.
Time is critical at this first
station.
Lose it and it's hard to make
up.
>> Got it, Jamie! Come on!
>> PROBST: Jamie still on the
first rope.
Brandon on the second rope.
Brandon has it.
Go!
( teams shout encouragement )
Bobby Jon quickly gets to work
on the log.
Yaxha with a big lead.
Jamie's still back on the first
rope, losing a lot of time for
Nakum.
>> Come on!
>> Switch rocks if you have to.
>> Come on, Jamie.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon getting
close.
>> Hit it, hit it!
>> PROBST: Nakum still back at
the first station.
Jamie having a heck of a time.
Bobby Jon nearly through.
Jamie still struggling.
>> Come on, Bobby, come on,
Bobby, come on, Bobby!
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon releases
the second batch of handles.
Jamie through the first rope.
One more to go.
>> Come on, Jamie.
>> PROBST: Up the platform with
all four handles.
>> Go, go, go! Go! Go!
>> Over here, buddy.
>> PROBST: Yaxha really wants
this reward and has a huge lead.
Jamie still back at the first
station.
Nakum very frustrated.
>> Go, Yaxha!
>> PROBST: Yaxha-- margaritas,
chip and dip, cage to swim in.
>> Guacamole.
>> PROBST: Guacamole!
Jamie still back at the first
station.
One of the biggest blowouts thus
far in Survivor: Guatemala.
That cart getting closer and
closer for Yaxha.
Jamie not giving up, but not
anywhere close to finishing.
>> Keep going, buddy.
>> PROBST: Judd's turned his
back.
>> Bang it, man!
>> PROBST: Yaxha very close.
Two more pulls and they'll be
there.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Go.
>> Pull!
>> PROBST: All six in the cart.
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: Yaxha going to cruise
past Nakum.
>> ( whooping )
>> PROBST: And there they go.
>> PROBST: Yaxha wins reward!
>> Yeah, buddy! Man!
>> PROBST: Jamie still working
on the rope.
>> I got it.
>> Good work, Jamie.
>> Y'all wanna finish?
>> It's okay, Jamie.
>> You just untie this and...
>> Just leave it go.
>> Y'all want to quit?
>> Jamie, the challenge is over.
>> We're not quitting.
We're done.
>> You finished the job, guy.
You finished.
>> I'm good.
>> Sorry, guys.
>> PROBST: Yaxha, great victory.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Great reward:
Pitcher of margaritas, chips,
healthy portion of dip, swim
cage with a deck, lounge chairs,
umbrella-- should make for a
nice, refreshing afternoon.
Congratulations.
Nakum, an absolute blowout.
Jamie, it falls on you.
Head on back to camp.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Oh, yeah!
Oh, man, look, at this!
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Whoo! Is that awesome.
Today, Yaxha, we're superstars.
>> This is amazing.
The reward was spectacular.
Look at this setup, man!
Oh, my God!
>> No crocodiles in that water.
>> Oh, man!
I'm so excited about the dang
thing.
It's a huge pool with, like,
lounge chairs.
The whole thing is caged in.
I thought it was going to be
like one cage for one person.
We all fit in there.
I didn't imagine it was going to
be that good.
>> Jackpot, baby!
>> Take everything on it and
enjoy.
>> Cheers.
>> God.
>> Brandon, you kick butt.
>> He made that contest not even
fun.
>> Man, I was hacking at that
rope.
I was just practically bashing
it apart.
You could say that I won it for
Yaxha.
I mean, I'm not trying to take
all the credit or anything.
But gotta go in there and give
it 110 percent, you know...
Give it your all.
>> Why didn't anybody on the
other team tell Jamie to chop?
>> I don't know.
>> Not one of them said "chop."
Brandon used that rock like
an ax on that rope.
We've got a new superhero on our
team.
I know Kansas is loving him and
so am I.
>> This is to kicking ass and
staying...
( all whooping, shouting )
>> Yaxha, baby!
>> There you go, Brian.
>> Oh, my God.
God, to just, like, sink into
the water... no, but I got to
keep eating.
I can't go in yet.
We are having an amazing day.
Yaxha is on cloud nine right
now.
>> Oh, man, Gary goes all in!
How deep is that?
>> Oh, my God, this is the best.
( all laughing, shouting )
>> The Guatemalan sun, 120
degrees, it's a killer out here.
We've been wanting to swim for
the longest time.
I'm a fish back home.
I love the water.
So to be able to swim, even in
a tiny square... is heaven.
>> One, two, three, Yaxha!
( all whooping )
>> There was no way in hell you
were going to bang it with that
little rock, so...
>> I could, like, I tried to
bang it.
It wouldn't bang, you know.
>> Don't worry about it.
>> That kid was an animal though
with that thing.
It was a hard challenge, you
know?
I just feel bad to lose, you
That was a good reward and I
lost it.
But no one could cut rope as
quick as Brandon can.
I take all of the blame.
>> You did the best you could
and that's all the tribe asks.
>> That's it, brother.
That's it, Jamie.
>> You did a great job.
>> Jamie apologized to
everybody, but I can see in
people's faces that they...
it's just like, man, what the
hell, what the hell did he do,
man?
We just got our asses kicked.
You know, we're a team, man.
You can't fall apart.
You can't blame anybody.
A team doesn't work like that.
Jamie, he tried every freakin'
thing he could do.
What are you gonna do, man?
>> None of us could have done
anything more.
>> I just thought it was going
to take... I knew the technique,
but I thought...
>> Well, if you know the
technique, then you got to step
up, man.
>> No, but I don't have the
shoulder and upper body strength
that you or Jamie would have.
>> I'm just saying, by all
means, if you and Margaret ever
want to step up to the plate,
man, be my guest, man.
You step up to the damn plate
and you do what you gotta do and
get one of us out of the spot...
>> I understand.
If you think you can do better,
then do it-- right.
>> You go at it, man.
>> I understand that.
>> Get us out of the spotlight
for a little bit and shine like
the star that you think you are.
That's it, man.
That's all I'm saying.
>> When we got back from the
challenge, Judd was mouthing
off about if you think you can
do something better, it's time
to step up, don't put all the
weight on all the guys.
So it made me really mad.
Some of these people are just
going out of their way to
irritate the other ones, and
I just don't think that's a very
smart thing.
>> Bobby Jon's in the cart
kicking his legs, cheering like
a frickin' girl.
I wanted to knock him out.
I'm happy for Bobby Jon, that
he's winning, because I know how
it is to lose, and it sucks.
But it annoys me when I watch
him win.
He cheers like a freakin' girl.
So, I think it's obnoxious.
And I think...
I'm jealous, basically.
He's so gay.
He gets so gay.
I can't stand it.
>> He's overly dramatic.
>> Right, like, get over it.
>> I didn't know how to cut that
rope that way.
>> Can't do it all, kid.
>> No, no way.
>> Jamie is a very cocky kind of
guy.
He's, like, "I can cut rope with
a rock, no problem.
I can fly right through that."
And he gets in there and gets
his ass beat by a 22-year-old
farm boy who basically saws
through the rope in, like, 30
seconds.
They get the whole challenge
done and frickin' Jamie can't
even cut the second rope.
You don't have to make it that
thin.
I'm just pissed.
I mean, I'm sick of losing.
I can't do this again, but I am
just trying really hard, when
I'm up in camp, to keep my mouth
shut.
I'm never going to cry in front
of any of them, ever.
I'm never going to tell them how
I really feel, but deep down in
me, my heart is breaking.
I mean, inside, I'm like
collapsing really.
Whew!
I just feel like I'm a really
bad...
I'm in a really bad dream and I
can't get out, no matter what.
( thunder crashing )
>> Whoa!
>> Oh, my God.
>> I do not want to relive what
I just went through on Palau.
And the same thing is happening
over again.
For some reason, the group I'm
always in is the less able
group, and the group that
basically... sucks.
>> It's been raining for a
couple hours, maybe an hour
or something like that.
We're huddled under a frickin'
umbrella and it sucks.
>> Somehow, Brian and Blake are
still sleeping, man, under the
shelter that we've got, and we
couldn't sleep under it worth a
damn, and somehow, those guys
haven't come out yet.
Either they found a dry spot or
they're just beefing through the
wetness and the rain.
>> Golden boy.
>> It's like, ♪ ahh... ♪
I came up with the name Golden
Boy for Blake 'cause he always
comes up smelling like roses.
He's going to make out great in
life, you know?
That's just him.
Plus, he also has the greatest
stories.
>> I started skydiving...
>> Really?
>> Yeah, I've got about 70
skydives in.
State champion tennis player
in high school...
Now I'm 24 and not married.
I was dating a lot and now
I have a girlfriend, a pretty
amazing girl.
I see a lot of older women, and
that kind of got me in trouble
for a while.
So it was like, I slowed that
down and...
>> Blake talks about himself all
the time.
All this, you know, he seems
like Captain America.
He's always talking himself up.
It's like, you know, God.
>> My girlfriend, she's got
double D.
She's got big boobs.
>> Really?
>> But then she got the pill and
they get bigger.
Geez, they just keep growing.
They were D's and now, they're
like almost double D's.
>> Man, that's too big.
That's gross.
>> I'm not even a boob man.
Bobby Jon and I were talking.
We're legs and ass kind of guys.
Brandon?
>> Novelty-size boobs, I don't
know about that.
>> Anyway, we went to Victoria's
Secret...
>> Blake is such an idiot.
He has to make himself look like
such a pretty boy, frat boy,
wealthy boy-- it's great.
I have a new favorite game out
here.
It's called "Bait Blake."
Blake, what is your absolute
best drunk story?
>> Oh, God.
My roommate-- we were all gone
all summer at camp, I thought
I'd have a party at my place.
We're doing shots, everybody's
getting hammered...
>> I'm trying to make sure he
tells all his stories around
people like Danni and Bobby Jon
so they see what a moron Blake
is.
This is awesome.
>> So what you're saying, Blake,
is that I wouldn't want one of
my three daughters to date you?
>> No, no.
I'm pretty feisty, Gary.
You wouldn't want 'em anywhere
near me.
>> He's just digging himself
into a hole, and I am gonna do
everything I can to make sure
he has a shovel.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh-oh, tree mail.
>> Oh, geez.
>> Look like something Hercules
would throw over the head.
>> Maybe we have to throw that.
>> ( hooting )
>> "Half your bodies, half your
minds, will have to move as one.
Communicate or fall apart,
Work together, this could be
fun.
Race around, push and shove,
Will old friends be respected?
Fail to catch immunity, you may
be the next one here ejected."
We just got tree mail.
It looks like it's going to be
very strenuous.
I have unfortunately seemed to
have been on one tribe that was
on a losing streak, and now I
got switched up and I'm on
another tribe that just recently
lost.
So I'm trying to get this bad
luck that is dwelling over my
head away from me.
>> Are we ready, guys?
Are we psyched?
>> I'm ready.
>> Yeah.
♪ Here we come to save the day!
The Nakum tribe is on their way.
And I will cut some fruits for
you. ♪
>> Lydia's drunk.
>> So many things have been, you
know, getting us down and out
lately.
And this morning I got up and I
said to myself, you know, forget
about all this crap about being
down and out.
You know, I'm going to be a
motivated person today.
Oh, disappeared.
( laughing )
You know, let's party on.
Listen, it's miserable out here.
Mosquitoes everywhere and...
Do the pancake!
( rhythmic singing )
>> Whip it, whip it, whip it!
>> Go, Rafe, go, Rafe, go Rafe!
>> And flip it...
>> Do it now, uh-huh.
>> What the hell happened to you
between yesterday and today?
Where is Lydia and when do we
get her back?
>> We need a little bit of that
this morning, don't you think?
>> You look like you're having a
seizure, though.
>> Elvis may be the king of rock
'n' roll, but I'm the queen.
Whoo!
Shut up.
( laughing )
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
How's everybody doing?
>> Great.
>> PROBST: Danni, how is this
tribe doing as a group?
>> We're having a great time.
Swimming by the pool has really
brought us all together.
We're really doing...
We're doing great.
>> PROBST: Nakum, nobody is
smiling.
Jamie looks irritated, Judd
looks frustrated, Margaret looks
ticked off.
That's just what I'm seeing.
Am I wrong, Jamie?
>> We're hungry for the win.
We're not smiling until we win.
We're mad right now.
>> PROBST: The reason I asked
about how you guys are getting
along, is that is critical in
today's challenge.
You have to work well together.
The tribe that does that the
best will win immunity.
The tribe that doesn't,
deservedly, will go to Tribal
Council and vote somebody out.
Let's get to today's immunity
challenge.
First things first.
Immunity, back up for grabs.
Here's how today's challenge
will work.
Each tribe will divide into two
groups of three.
Those groups will take a spot
downfield and you'll be holding
a Maya catch net.
That leaves one tribe member
from each tribe.
They will alternate launching
balls from a catapult downfield
while the groups maneuver to try
to catch the ball.
You can catch any ball from
either tribe member at any time.
The first tribe with five
catches wins immunity.
Losers, Tribal Council, somebody
going home.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Brian is launcher for Yaxha,
Lydia for Nakum.
Brian's up first.
Makes his selection.
Places the ball in the trough.
He is locked and loaded.
Once the ball is in the air, you
can leave your mat.
Brian takes his aim far right.
And he launches.
Heading towards Bobby Jon, Gary
and Danni.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Score for Yaxha.
>> Good job, Yaxha.
>> PROBST: Yaxha leads.
One, zip.
Lydia takes her first shot.
>> Come on, Lydia!
>> PROBST: Lydia takes a spot at
the catapult, takes a little
aim.
Her first shot and it's
launched.
It's deep.
>> Right, right, right.
>> PROBST: Oh, Yaxha had a shot
at it, couldn't do it.
>> You guys, we gotta be a
little faster.
Yeah, but I got to box it, too,
man.
>> I know, but listen to me,
because it's going deep.
They'll never get near us.
>> PROBST: Steph, Judd and Rafe
talking it through.
Brian's up.
Brian takes his aim.
And he launches high and short.
>> Got it, got it, got it!
Got it, got it, got it!
>> PROBST: Nakum steals one.
Judd, Rafe and Steph!
We're tied, one-one.
Playing to five.
Lydia.
>> All the way, Lydia.
>> PROBST: Lydia going right
back to the same spot.
And it's in the air.
The tribes moving.
Brandon hits the deck.
Nobody gets it.
Good defense by Yaxha.
>> It's all right.
>> PROBST: Still tied.
Brian up.
>> Turn it as much as you can,
Bri.
>> I got it.
>> You guys, get ready to back
up, they're on the left.
>> PROBST: Brian takes his aim,
far right.
He launches it quickly towards
Gary, Danni and Bobby Jon.
But they can't connect.
Stephenie plowed into Bobby Jon.
>> They didn't catch it.
>> PROBST: Lydia going back to
the same spot.
Lydia launches one deep toward
Rafe, Judd and Steph...
and they connect!
>> Yes!
Nakum leads, two-one.
Brian up for Yaxha.
Yaxha connects.
Yaxha ties it up.
Two, two.
>> Good job, Bri.
>> PROBST: Lydia, quick aim.
She launches.
It's deep.
Nakum could get it.
And they do.
>> Whoo! Yeah!
>> Good shot, Lydia!
>> PROBST: Nakum back in the
lead, three, two.
Brian up.
Immunity on the line.
>> I'm not looking, I'm just
going straight back, you guys.
>> PROBST: He launches.
>> Got it, got it, got it.
Nakum steals one.
>> Wow!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Nakum leads.
Four, two.
Lydia.
>> This is it, Nakum.
>> PROBST: Nakum could win it
here.
>> Yaxha, knock 'em down.
>> PROBST: Yaxha needs to steal
one.
Launches it.
For the win if Nakum gets it...
And they do!
Nakum wins immunity!
>> Who's smiling now?
Who's smiling now?
>> Whoo!
>> Yes! Lydia!
Come here! You!
You did it!
( whooping, shouting )
>> Go get that...
>> PROBST: Nakum... immunity.
A break from Tribal Council.
Hopefully that will lift the
spirits a little bit.
Yaxha-- other end of the
spectrum, somebody going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
See you at Tribal.
Head on back.
>> It was our time to lose.
>> This doesn't feel very good.
>> No, it don't.
>> Jamie's like, "Who's the
baller now?
Who's the baller now?"
>> I didn't even hear him say
that.
>> I'm like, "Jamie, why don't
you just shut up and go cut a
rope or something?"
>> All that frustration on that
rope came out.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Oh, that burns me up.
There's a way to win and there's
a way to lose.
He's from Georgia, too.
Alabama, Georgia kind of have
rivals.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> We lost immunity, which was
disappointing.
The Yaxha tribe is going into
Tribal Council tonight with four
old Nakum members and three old
Yaxha members.
So the math is right there.
It's four to three.
So you would think that it would
be either me, Gary or Amy going
tonight, and it very well may
be.
What have you been hearing?
>> Nobody is talking to me.
They don't talk about
alliances...
I know that Blake's driving
everybody crazy.
>> So, hopefully...
>> So, I know Danni and Brandon
and Bobby Jon are pretty tight
>> Yeah. We are at risk.
I don't know what they're going
to do.
But would you be okay voting for
Blake?
>> Oh, in a second.
He's driving everybody crazy.
>> I really feel like Danni
would vote for Blake before
she'd vote for me or you.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> I hope.
>> We've just got to make sure
that one of them votes for
Blake, yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Good, good, good.
>> This Blake thing, driving
everybody crazy has been really
good for us Yaxha members.
Our only hope in the game is to
get somebody to turn from the
original Nakum against Blake.
I just want to see somebody
that's hard-working that has a
good attitude win it.
>> Mm-hmm, I feel the same way.
>> You know?
You hate to see somebody get
to the final four that doesn't
deserve it.
We just can't let that happen
this time.
You know, I do agree that's
best, though if that needs
to happen.
I just don't want to start, you
know, going back on words and
all that.
I've given Blake my word that,
you know, I wouldn't vote for
him.
But I listen to Gary a lot
because he's smart and he knows
about team unity.
I do know there's going to be
some times where I am going to
have to switch my vote, and I
feel like right now is not one
of those times.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I know you're with him from
the beginning.
>> I feel the same way.
>> I talked to Bobby Jon.
>> What did he say?
>> He wants to vote for Brian.
>> I think maybe Bobby Jon
thinks we all have an alliance,
which we do not.
None of us were aligned
originally.
>> No. At this point in the
game, I want good people to go
forward.
>> Yeah.
>> I want Blake gone first.
>> Gary came up to me to talk
about Blake.
And Gary just said he couldn't
vote for somebody who didn't
deserve to go any further, so I
said I felt is same way and I
just needed to go talk to the
rest of the team.
>> Gary swears he's with us.
>> You've talked to him about
it?
>> I've talked to him about it.
>> I'm going to tell you right
now, I'm not going to vote for
Blake.
You know, because we're strong.
We got 'em... right now.
I'm probably going to vote
for... I don't know, Amy or
Brian.
>> Lights come on, pull
over, gives us both a warning
for not having proper signal
devices and whistles.
I'm like, dude, we rented these
for two hours.
We don't live here.
We live in south, downtown
Dallas.
>> You know, the whole Blake
situation, we're not sure what's
going to happen with that.
Everybody is getting a little
fed up with him.
I like the guy, he's a good guy.
He's just young and it's just
typical frat boy stuff.
I don't like that frat boy stuff
at all.
>> Yeah, the girl I almost lost
my virginity to.
So they're...
>> But he's really valuable
because he's so athletic.
He's great in challenges.
Brandon and Bobby Jon said they
wouldn't vote for him.
And so it kind of comes down to
my vote.
And I hate being the swing vote.
I mean, it's just... that's a
part of the game I just don't
like.
Because it's going to hurt
peoples' feelings, but it has to
happen.
Unfortunately it's just the way
it goes sometimes.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Tribal
Council.
Before we get started, how bad
was the storm last night, Gary?
>> The storm was terrible.
It was definitely a character-
building night.
Two of us slept through the
whole thing, so they got some
sleep, but everybody else was
out at the fire trying to keep
the fire going.
>> PROBST: Who slept?
>> Brian and Blake.
>> In my defense, I woke up and
took the late shift.
>> I just figured, they're
standing by the fire, trying
to stay warm.
They're just cold, wet and
miserable.
I was like, I'm getting lucky in
here.
I'm ridin' the rain out.
I thought everybody would come
back in and join me.
I didn't think it would be an
entire night out there.
>> Golden boy.
>> PROBST: Is that your
nickname?
>> She did give me a nickname.
>> PROBST: Golden Boy?
>> Golden Boy, no matter what,
comes out shining.
He's the Golden Boy with the
golden flag-- ah!-- and that
sparkle in his tooth.
>> PROBST: Blake, you're a guy
that was gasping for air.
You had your arms on your chest
going... and now you're Golden
Boy?
>> I crashed and now, you know,
I have perked up.
I've got my wind back in my
sails.
I just think it was something
my body had to go through.
Luckily, I'm feeling better and
now I think I'm ready to ride
out to the end.
>> PROBST: Brandon, day 14.
The social aspect of this game
is starting to pick up.
It's a lot more than just
physical challenges.
Are you seeing that increase?
>> Yeah.
I'd say it is starting to ramp
up a little.
I mean, getting to know these
people a little bit more.
You start to like people a
little bit more than others.
>> PROBST: Gary, two tribes
merged.
There's four former Nakum, three
former Yaxha.
What were those first few
moments like and how are they
different now?
>> The first few moments were
pretty scary because you don't
know where you stand.
The numbers are against you.
And trying to get to know
everybody was just like they won
over again.
>> PROBST: Amy, do you feel like
this is two groups of people
living together?
>> Well, I'm thinking we're one
group and forget what happened
before.
This is my tribe and this is who
I'm loyal to.
Obviously we're at a
disadvantage, but you just try
to do the best you can.
>> PROBST: Blake, is that the
same for you?
Are you guys one tribe and to
heck with what happened before
this?
>> We've all come together as
seven in the last few days,
but, yeah, I mean, there's
definitely bonds that I've
formed with Danni and Bobby
and Brandon that I haven't
gotten to experience with these
guys.
That'll certainly influence me
to some extent.
>> PROBST: Brian, what do you
guys have to do to encourage
this group to think as a group
and not down tribal lines?
>> If that's their game plan,
just to pick us off, I'm sorry
that it is, because we're good
people and we should take the
time to get to know one another
before you make such a snap
judgment.
So, if it's me tonight, I'm
afraid I'm a victim of a
minority.
>> PROBST: Bobby Jon, tonight's
vote tough, easy, indifferent?
>> Every Tribal Council is a
tough vote for me.
Everybody in their own way
fought to get here, and
somebody's about to go home
tonight.
Their journey is about to end.
So, you know, I don't like
ending somebody's dream.
I like to keep the dream alive.
>> PROBST: Okay.
It is time to vote.
Bobby Jon, you're up.
>> You may be the Golden Boy,
but I'm platinum.
I hope it's you.
>> You know, I think of the
three people on the original
Yaxha team, you're the weakest
right now.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Blake.
Brian.
One vote Blake, one vote Brian.
Two votes Brian, one vote Blake.
Blake.
Two votes Blake, two votes
Brian.
Blake.
Three votes Blake, two votes
Brian.
The fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala, Blake.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Blake, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Bye, guys.
>> PROBST: Well, I'd say based
on tonight's vote, this game
just took a big shift.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time, on
Survivor: At Nakum, Margaret
and Judd just can't get along.
>> Judd is irritating.
>> She just can't grasp the fact
that the old tribe ain't coming
back.
>> PROBST: Amy takes another
blow.
Amy's down.
Amy is hurt.
And Bobby Jon and Jamie square
off.
>> I didn't see it coming.
I don't understand the reason
for why, and that's why I'm
kind of perplexed right now,
and I'm kind of angry.
You know, I've stepped it up in
a few challenges, and I think
that they were just trying
to get out somebody strong.
Why would you do that?
That makes no sense.
But, you know, you don't want
all the strong players, I guess,
but again, playing the odds, I
don't understand why it