>> JEFF: Previously on
Survivor:
In the jungles of Guatemala,
among the ruins of an
ancient civilization, 16
Americans began their
adventure with a big surprise.
Come on out.
I'm sure you guys recognize
Bobby Jon and Stephenie from
Survivor Palau.
Stephenie is a member of Yaxha.
Bobby Jon is a member of Nakum.
>> We were just thrilled to have
Bobby Jon because he's not going
to quit for anything.
I was like, oh, we're winning.
We got Stephenie, like,
we're good to go.
>> JEFF: But some weren't so
sure.
>> How am I going to win a
million now that she's here?
>> JEFF: The tribes immediately
faced off in their first
reward challenge.
It's a grueling 11-mile race
through the jungles of
Guatemala.
The winning tribe claims the
right to the better camp;
they also get flint to make
fire.
Survivors, ready, go!
And the game was on.
>> Got to make time.
You drop it, you leave it,
you go.
>> On Stephenie's Yaxha tribe,
Gary kept his true identity
a secret.
>> Gary, what do you do?
>> All right!
I was in the NFL for 11 years.
My real name is Gary Hogeboom.
If somebody does recognize me,
Just gonna say that's not me.
I'm Gary Hawkins.
>> JEFF: And Bobby Jon's Nakum
tribe faced a setback when Blake
got hurt.
>> MARGARET: One of these trees
that have briars that
look like spikes actually broke
on Blake's shoulder.
That really took him down a
couple notches.
>> JEFF: After a grueling night
in the jungle...
>> Guys, wait, wait, wait,
please.
JEFF: The tribes stayed close.
>> They're catching up, they're
behind us.
>> We need to, like, get right
on their ass, if not pass them.
>> JEFF: With Yaxha on their
heels, Bobby Jon's Nakum tribe
narrowly pulled it off.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> JEFF: Congratulations.
The losing Yaxha was sent out to
find their camp.
You've got more paddling to do.
Even though they had no flint
to make fire, Yaxha made the
best of their situation.
>> I am so psyched.
Finally, I'm on a tribe that's
got as much heart and
determination as me.
>> JEFF: Back at Nakum, the
victory had come at a high
price.
>> ( retching )
>> You okay back there?
Breathe through your nose,
Blake.
>> Bobby Jon?
>> Huh?
His eyes are rolling back
>> We have these big strong
guys, strong as oxes, and
they're all down.
>> JEFF: At the first immunity
challenge, the Yaxha spirit
secured them a victory...
Yaxha wins immunity!
...sending a depleted
Nakum to Tribal Council.
Though Blake, Judd and Bobby Jon
were physically ailing,
Jim was the worst off and was
voted out of the tribe.
>> Jim, the tribe has spoken.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> A rock, a rock.
Watch, watch, watch.
Has anybody found the trail yet?
>> This is a place where you
could break your leg,
your ankle.
>> Tonight we had Tribal
Council, and it seems like
that's where I live.
It seems like I'm paying rent at
Tribal Council.
I'm waiting for it to change.
>> You know what.
Just go lay down, okay?
>> ( coughing )
>> We just don't have the energy
to suffer the emotional hit--
the physical hit is bad enough.
The emotional toll that Tribal
Council takes on you is
terrible.
It's just a sick, sick feeling
knowing we had to go and even
worse coming back.
( coughing )
>> They just don't look like
they're having fun.
>> They are so serious and they
are not like buddy-buddy,
you know?
>> I'm telling you, it's Bobby
Jon.
He's so damn serious.
>> It's day four and we're
getting to know each other
really well.
We all have different qualities.
We have an amazing tribe.
>> Better to be diverse like we
are.
>> We got the most diverse group
there.
We got a bum.
We got a police officer.
We got a magician's assistant.
We got a fish monger.
We got a gay guy and we got a
landscaper-- but we all come
together and it's brilliant.
>> Are you guys cold, or no?
>> No, but a tarantula jumped on
my arm.
>> A tarantula?
How big?
>> About that big.
>> You saw a tarantula?
>> GARY: You know, they've asked
me what I do, and I told them I
was a landscaper, not a
quarterback.
Nobody has asked me what I did
15 years ago, so I guess I don't
have to tell them.
>> All right.
Head back.
>> Want one or two?
>> You braiding hair?
>> I want to French braid yours.
I want to learn how to do it.
>> No?
>> You want to learn on my head?
Why you want to learn on my
head?
It's just like a fun camp life
It's much different from
anything I had experienced
before
So I think the fact that we get
along so well is huge,
Cause we do have good team
morale.
It's become like a family, and
we're hoping to keep that family
together for a long time.
>> Got some tree mail, folks.
>> Want me to read it?
>> Go ahead.
>> Yeah.
>> "Hunger is a burden.
You need energy to compete.
You've been caught in a web of
hardship.
Winning this one will help you
eat."
>> We just got tree mail, and
that's the last thing I wanted
to hear.
For some reason I just can't
breathe, and I've been
struggling for the last
three or four days.
I haven't slept and so forth,
and drinking water doesn't seem
to help.
>> Blake...
Lay down, hon.
Lay down if you feel short of
breath.
>> I can't breathe.
>> I'm really, really worried
about Blake.
He's a strong, you know,
young guy.
He's heaving.
He's struggling to get breaths
and something's not right.
>> ( gasping )
>> Breathe through your nose.
Breathe through your nose.
>> Oh, God.
>> We got you-- okay.
>> It's okay.
>> Blake, like, he is-- I don't
think he can really handle it
out here, because he's just, you
know, on his hands and knees and
just breathing hard and has been
having problems the whole time
we've been out here.
>> Blake, are you going to be
able to do it?
>> I ain't got anything against
the guy.
I think he's a good guy and
everything, but I'm more one of
those, like a tougher guy which,
you know, you're hurting and
everything, but you've just got
to man up.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
Yaxha getting your first look at
the new Nakum.
Jim, voted out at the first
Tribal Council.
All right.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: It is for reward.
Here's how it works.
On my go, you will race one at a
time up a ramp, across the net
run, out on to a rope spider
web.
Attached to the web are eight
bags.
Crawling underneath the web
you'll attempt to retrieve a
bag.
Once you have a bag, drop
yourself into the water, make
your way back.
If you fall into the water
without a bag, you've got to
come back to the start--
next person goes.
Everybody must attempt this
course at least once.
After that, you can go in any
order you want and send whoever
you want.
First tribe to retrieve all
eight bags wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Fishing items.
>> Wow.
>> JEFF: Worms.
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: Filet knife.
Lots of hooks, corks, weights,
twine.
Because, in addition to the
crocs, there are lots of fish in
that lake.
Yaxha, you have one extra
member.
You're sitting somebody out.
Keeping mind you cannot sit
out the same person in back-to-
back challenges.
Who's sitting out?
Amy, You're going to sit this
one out?
>> Right.
>> Take your spots.
Wait for my go.
>> JEFF: All right, guys.
First two up at the red start.
Jamie and Bobby Jon.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready.
Go!
>> Go, Jamie!
>> Go, go, go!
>> Jamie!
>> There you go, Jamie, you got
it.
>> Go up the center.
Go up the center.
>> Jamie!
>> JEFF: Jamie making quick work
of it.
Bobby Jon trying to hang on.
Jamie at his bag.
Bobby Jon closing in on a bag.
>> Jamie!
>> JEFF: Jamie has his bag.
He's in the water and heading
back.
Bobby Jon right behind.
He's got his bag.
>> Come on, Jamie!
>> JEFF: He's in the water
heading back.
>> Yeah, Jamie, come on!
>> Come on, Jamie!
Nice work!
>> JEFF: Brian on the course for
Yaxha.
Bobby Jon taking a long time
getting back, losing a lot of
ground for Nakum.
>> Let's go, Bobby Jon!
Brian going straight up the big
rope.
>> Go Brian!
>> JEFF: Cindy on the course for
Nakum, a lot of ground to make
up.
>> Go, Cindy!
>> JEFF: Brian going for a near
bag.
>> Come on, Brian!
You got it, baby!
>> JEFF: Cindy right on top of
Brian.
>> Good girl!
>> JEFF: Brian has a bag, Cindy
has a bag.
>> Come on, Brian!
>> JEFF: Cindy made up a lot of
time for Nakum.
>> Yeah, Cindy!
>> JEFF: Cindy giving Nakum the
lead.
Blake and Stephenie on the
course.
Trying to figure out a strategy,
best way to work this web.
Blake moving quickly, Steph
fighting hard.
>> Come on, Steph!
Steph knows what bag she's going
for.
Blake at his bag, trying to
untie it.
Stephenie at her bag, trying to
Blake has his.
Stephenie has hers!
We're still dead-even with the
third bag.
Stephenie first up the ladder.
Yaxha is back in the lead now.
>> Here we go, guys!
You're doing great!
>> JEFF: Gary for Yaxha.
Brandon out for Nakum.
Yaxha with a bit of a lead.
Gary is gonna have to make his
way deep for a deep bag.
Brandon really working the
course, going all the way to the
back, Gary right there with him.
Both Gary and Brandon untying
their bags, Brandon has his.
He's heading back.
>> JEFF: Gary has his bag and a
big splash in the water.
Margaret on the course for
Nakum.
>> Come on, Gary.
>> JEFF: Gary back with the
fourth bag for Yaxha.
Rafe on the course for Yaxha.
Rafe knows right where he's
heading.
Margaret untying her bag.
>> Let's go, Margaret!
>> JEFF: She has it... Nakum
still with the lead.
Rafe struggling to hang on.
>> You got it, Rafe!
>> JEFF: Rafe can't hang on.
That's going to hurt Yaxha.
>> Come on, Rafe!
>> JEFF: Margaret able to get a
bag.
Rafe unable to get a bag.
Could be the difference.
>> Come on, Rafe.
>> JEFF: Rafe struggling to get
up the ladder.
Nakum, now with a one-bag lead.
Judd on the course for Nakum.
Judd takes a header into the
net.
Rafe still cannot get back up
the ladder.
>> Come on, Rafe.
>> Come on, Rafe!
>> JEFF: Rafe, got to pull
yourself up.
Judd, hanging on.
Getting inventive.
He's still in.
>> Come on, Rafe!
Yaxha losing a lot of ground.
>> Come on, Rafe.
>> JEFF: Rafe's finally up.
Four days and no water really
taking its toll.
>> Come on, Rafe!
Morgan on the course trying to
make up some ground.
>> Go, Morgan!
Nakum leads five bags-four.
>> Judd, he's dropped.
Drop.
>> JEFF: Judd is in the water.
Judd cannot get a bag.
A chance for Yaxha to catch up.
Morgan needs to get a bag on
this one.
Judd heading back.
Danni on the course for Nakum.
>> Come on, Morgan, you got
this!
>> JEFF: Bags are deep on the
course.
It's a lot of climbing now.
>> Yes, Morgan, yes!
>> JEFF: Morgan's at a bag.
>> Come on, Danni.
>> JEFF: Morgan has the fifth
bag for Yaxha.
Got to get back quickly.
Brianna waiting for her shot.
>> Good job, good job, good job!
>> JEFF: We are tied five bags
each.
Brianna on the course for Yaxha.
>> Here we go, Brianna!
>> JEFF: All the bags now at the
far end of the spider web.
Brianna-- got to hang on.
>> You can do it!
>> JEFF: Brianna can't hang on.
Once again, Yaxha unable to get
a bag.
Big advantage for Nakum.
Brianna has got to get back.
>> Let's go, Danni!
>> JEFF: Lydia on the course for
Yaxha.
Maybe she can get a bag.
Danni has a bag.
>> Danni!
>> Come on, girl!
Come on, Danni!
Get the last!
Come on, let's go!
>> JEFF: Danni coming back with
the sixth bag for Nakum.
>> Come on, Danni!
Come on, girl!
>> JEFF: Nakum leads six bags to
five.
Brooke on the course for Nakum.
>> Go, Brooke!
>> JEFF: Lydia at a bag for
Yaxha.
Working around the outside of
the course.
Lydia with the sixth bag for
Yaxha.
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: Brooke got a bag now!
>> Come on, Lydia!
>> JEFF: We are tied six bags
each.
Jamie on the course.
Brooke untying the knot.
>> Come on, Brooke!
>> JEFF: Brooke has it.
>> Go, go, go.
>> JEFF: Lets herself in
the water.
Jamie now with his bag,
Brooke trying to get up the
ladder.
Can't slow down now.
Jamie has his bag.
Jamie in the water.
Jamie made up a tremendous
amount of time.
We are tied seven bags each.
Blake on the course.
Brian now on the course.
Coming down to the final bag.
Blake making up a lot of time.
Blake at the eighth bag, Brian
got to get back to that bag,
time is slipping away, Brian
trying to get there as fast as
he can.
Blake has his bag, Brian at
his bag.
Got to get it untied.
Brian has his bag.
Brian and Blake both in the
water with the last bags.
Fishing gear at stake.
It's gonna be a race to the
finish.
Blake pulling himself up the
ladder.
>> Come on, Brian.
>> JEFF: Brian has got to move.
Got to move.
Nakum wins reward!
>> ( cheering )
>> JEFF: Nakum, obviously, you
could use some food, fishing
gear, worms.
Hopefully that will help you in
that endeavor.
Good effort.
Yaxha, close.
Both tribes have been neck-and-
neck in every challenge so far,
four days in.
Doesn't get you anything on this
one.
Head on back.
All right, guys, grab your
stuff, head on out.
>> We decided that we were going
to go fishing with our newly
acquired fishing gear, so, you
know, we got up at the
butt-crack of dawn.
We're like, all right, we're
gonna get us a big fish.
>> That steady on...?
>> Nice!
>> Good job.
>> Today, we were just so ready
to get on the boat.
I wanted to get out there and
fish so bad.
I'm feeling better a little bit
right now.
I'm not panting as much.
Just as long as I'm competitive
and I can play like I did
yesterday, I'm good.
>> I got one, I got one.
>> Yes, yes!
>> Breakfast.
What do you think's in these
things?
>> Maybe we should have some
corn, what do you think?
>> Excellent.
I was going to suggest that.
It'd be such a treat.
>> Yaxha is in desperation food
mode right now.
Everything out here we will try,
at least once.
What is that?
Oh, wow!
Does anyone want to eat a
grasshopper?
>> No.
>> That's a grasshopper?
>> That's a grasshopper.
>> That's a huge grasshopper.
>> It's a busy morning.
Everybody is working, except for
right now, I would say Morgan is
the one that's not doing as much
around the camp as everybody
else.
I love Morgan, but you've got to
work around camp if you want
tribe mates to be on your side.
>> ( swishing water )
>> I'm making a cove inlet, as
you can see.
It's pretty wide and a little
opening in the front there...
And after everything settles
I'll cover it up with a burlap
sack and I'll catch a little
protein.
We need some protein.
>> You want to eat ants?
>> I thought it was going to be
termites.
>> Yeah, I thought it was going
to be, too, but those are ants.
>> We need protein.
>> I'll eat ants.
Let's do it.
>> Okay, go.
>> I don't know.
>> Where did you get that nest
thing from?
>> Was there like millions?
>> I mean, we've probably got
like 200 ants here.
>> Rafe and Gary decided to go
get an ant nest because ants are
apparently full of protein,
which is so nasty.
>> What do you think?
I can't believe I'm eating ants
>> Ants can't bite, can they?
>> Yep.
>> Oh.
>> Mine almost had like a nice
little zing to them.
I'm not going to be eating ants
As long as I have corn and water
that's what I'll sustain myself
on until I win a food challenge.
>> You have any luck down there
with the burlap sack?
>> Ten little minnows.
>> You got ten minnows?
>> Little tiny guys, but it's
something.
>> That's a minnow each!
>> You are a work horse.
I think we need you.
>> What do you think, fish
monger, how long does a fish
like this go?
>> Fry it to a crisp.
>> We don't need those hooks
and lines.
>> Cheers, cheers.
>> Enjoy.
>> Oh! Mm-mm!
>> You know what they say, the
way to a man's heart is through
their stomachs.
Tastes like trout on a grill.
>> ( breathing deeply )
( mumbling )
( belches )
>> Let me tell you something
about Blake.
He does basically nothing in
camp.
I mean, the guy's a great guy,
but he does nothing in camp.
And then you got Margaret just
nurturing him all day.
>> Every time I turn around,
that's all I hear: Sit down
and relax.
Get some water.
Sit down, relax, get some water.
And I'm saying to myself, damn,
how much more relaxing does this
dude need, man?
The guy sleeps all day, man,
you know.
I'm getting screwed, man, me and
you bringing this damn water up
and going up there all...
lagged out, and arms can't even
move, man.
>> No, you're right.
>> I'm not going to be pulling
his weight all day.
Blake just rests all day,
man, it's just like a big rest
for him.
So he's got all of his strength
and his energy to go into these
challenges and these rewards.
That's what happens when you
rest all day.
You get that burst of energy,
man.
I want to be the hero next
challenge or next immunity, you
know.
I'm gonna be the hero.
>> Tree mail.
>> Ah, this is going to be fun.
>> "Blood, sweat, tears and mud.
A day you'll give it all.
Stretching, pulling, scraping,
clawing.
This could be a brawl!
The hardest work since you've
arrived, will happen here today.
You decide how much sweat to
give.
Tonight one more goes away."
Pretty much a tug-of-war.
>> That's what I'm thinking.
>> Or it's like this right here.
One right here and one right
here and just get down.
>> Right.
>> We have a lot of really good
athletes on our team, but Yaxha
has been right there in
everything.
Stephenie, we know, is an
amazing athlete.
I work in sports radio back in
Kansas City.
Gary used to be a professional
football player.
He was the quarterback.
Quarterbacks, though,
aren't usually as athletic as
the rest of the football
players, but, uh... ( laughs)
but he's been holding his own,
so we'll see what happens.
>> JEFF: Okay.
First things first.
Lydia, give it up.
Immunity back up for grabs.
Today's immunity challenge is a
good old-fashioned tug-of-war.
Both tribes will be connected to
each other with a common rope.
Your goal is to retrieve a tribe
flag.
There's a rope anchored at each
end of the field.
If you get to it, use it to pull
yourself to your flag.
At any time, tribe members from
either tribe can go back and try
to interfere with the other
tribe to impede their progress.
There is a time element to this
challenge.
If, after 15 minutes, neither
tribe has retrieved a single
flag, we'll move to a series of
one-on-one showdowns.
The tribe that wins this
challenge wins immunity,
guaranteed at least one more day
out here in hot Guatemala.
Losers, Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody going home.
Yaxha, you have one extra
member.
Sitting somebody out.
Amy sat out the last challenge,
cannot sit out in this one.
Brianna.
All right.
Everybody else, wait for my go.
Here we go.
Survivors ready...
go!
>> Come on.
>> JEFF: Nakum with a bit of a
lead, right off the bat.
Brian going back.
>> Pull, pull, pull!
>> JEFF: Danni and Brian having
a little shove off.
>> Play hard!
>> I'm playing hard!
>> Amy yelling at Brian to get
into it.
Danni, shoving him in the mud.
>> Pull, pull.
>> Pull, you guys.
>> JEFF: Margaret in on the
action.
>> Pull.
>> I got them both. Pull!
I'm holding two!
>> JEFF: Brian, Danni, having a
powwow in the middle.
Yaxha giving it everything they
have and not doing anything.
Immunity at stake.
Somebody going home tonight.
>> Pull.
Just walk in.
( groaning )
>> JEFF: Down to one minute left
in this round.
If neither tribe has a flag in
one minute we go to one-on-one.
Nakum, takes a sudden surge.
Get ahold of that rope and you
can pull yourselves in.
Yaxha, not giving up an inch.
We're winding this down.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Time!
Stop right there!
Got a stalemate.
All right.
We're moving on to a series of
one-on-one showdowns.
At the end of each showdown,
whichever tribe member is closer
to their flag, wins the flag.
Three flags wins immunity.
Any tribe member can go as many
rounds as they want.
Each round will last five
minutes.
Figure out who is going first.
Judd will go for Nakum.
Gary will be the one for Yaxha.
Here we go.
Challenge back on.
>> Come on, Gary.
>> Come on, Gary!
>> JEFF: Five minutes in this
round.
Closest to the flag gets it.
Nakum with a bit of an edge.
>> Go, go, go.
>> He's a quarterback.
You're like a linebacker, come
on.
>> JEFF: Judd has the rope.
Going to use it for leverage now
to pull himself closer.
>> Stay right there.
Don't use any more energy.
>> JEFF: Closest to the flag
gets it.
Gary makes a move for Judd,
gonna tackle him.
>> Hold on to the rope.
>> Don't let go.
>> JEFF: Neither guy giving up.
Five seconds, four, three, two,
one.
First flag goes to Nakum.
>> Great work, babe.
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: It's Brandon versus
Jamie, going for the second
flag.
Challenge back on.
>> Come on, Jamie.
>> JEFF: Jamie, making a surge,
gets a little bit of a lead.
Brandon making a move.
>> Go, go.
>> JEFF: Gaining a few inches on
Jamie.
Jamie trying to stay in.
Brandon digging in.
>> Jamie makes a move.
It backfired.
He falls down.
Brandon with a big lead now.
Jamie trying to get a hold.
He can't.
Brandon pulling Jamie, trying to
get to that rope for leverage.
He's got it.
Brandon pulling him in.
Brandon has the second flag for
Nakum!
( cheering )
>> JEFF: Nakum leads 2-zip.
It is Judd and Jamie.
Jamie is going to run again.
If Judd holds on to this lead,
Nakum wins immunity.
Yaxha goes to Tribal Council.
Here we go!
Challenge back on.
Right out of the gate,
Jamie makes a big move.
Yaxha has the lead.
>> Jamie!
Yeah!
( cheering )
>> JEFF: Jamie got a lot of
momentum and the lead.
( cheering )
>> Come on, Jamie!
>> JEFF: 30 seconds left.
Jamie trying to hold on to that
lead, but nobody moving
anywhere.
>> Come on, Judd!
>> JEFF: Judd's got to make a
move or Yaxha gets their first
flag.
Ten seconds, nine, eight, seven,
six, five...
Jamie relaxes.
Judd makes a big pull...
three, two, one.
This challenge is over.
Nakum wins immunity.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Nakum, who wants it?
Congratulations, immunity.
Safe out here at least one
more day.
Yaxha, different news for you.
First taste of Tribal Council.
Tonight you will vote out your
first member.
Grab your flag.
Head on back to camp.
>> RAFE: You know, it was a
rough challenge today.
We gave it everything that we
had, but we just couldn't pull
their big man, and so now we
got Tribal tonight.
>> That challenge was miserable.
>> This is only gonna tie up,
you guys.
We're not down.
>> Just clean up and have a good
dinner, drink a lot.
>> I'm completely nervous.
This game to me is one big bag
of nerves.
It's the worst thing ever.
You always have to be on your
toes.
You always have to be watching.
>> Where do you want it?
>> I mean, she's nice, everybody
here is nice.
I love everybody here to death,
I'm not, you know what I'm
saying...
But that's my first pick.
I'm just gonna tell you all,
'cause I trust y'all, you know.
>> GARY: Jamie said, hey, we got
to get Steph off.
The girls love her.
You know?
She's gonna get us all off of
here.
The thing about that is we've
got to keep strength on our side
for those challenges so we win
them.
>> They want to get rid of me?
Has anybody said that?
>> Yeah.
>> They want to get rid of me.
>> Girl, where you been?
>> What did they said?
>> They are talking about you.
>> Getting rid of me?
>> Yeah.
>> Really?
>> Who?
>> Are you kidding?
>> Jamie and them.
>> Yeah.
>> I never heard that.
>> Don't take it personally.
>> No, I'm not.
I'm shocked about that.
I guess it's just from
inexperience on Jamie's part,
and I'm not saying I'm a pro,
but this early, I mean, clearly
I am the strongest girl on the
team.
Why would they want to vote me
off first?
That's retarded.
I refuse to go early this time.
I refuse.
>> Gary, were you a former
NFL quarterback?
>> Me? No.
>> When I was tackling Danni and
we were like sitting there, she
goes, "You got a professional
NFL linebacker on your team"
and I said, "Who?"
And she goes, "Gary."
I was like...
She goes, I bet he hasn't told
you that.
I said, how do you know, and
she says "Oh, I'm a
sportscaster, so I know him from
then.
>> It was brought up by Danni
from Nakum that I played in the
NFL, quarterback, and she told
Brian that as they were
wrestling in the mud.
What the heck she was doing
telling him that while she was
wrestling in the mud, I don't
know, trying to disturb our
tribe, I'll bet.
>> That's pretty funny.
>> Yeah, well, Danni is a
sportscaster.
>> Somebody needs to knock her
out.
>> GARY: I'm just going to deny
and see how it goes.
I'll play it by ear, because I
think I'd be voted off
immediately.
>> Everybody is going around--
What do we do? What do we do?
What do we do?
The two that I'm thinking about
are Lydia and Morgan.
Lydia is limited in the
challenges compared to Morgan.
But Morgan doesn't do very much
in camp.
>> Morgan or Lydia.
>> It's got to be Morgan, I
think.
>> But Morgan in an obstacle
course is much quicker.
I love Lydia.
I'm only saying Lydia because
I love her, but Morgan is much
more athletic.
>> All right, longevity-wise
who do you think will be better?
...to get us to...
>> Morgan, we can pick up
like Lydia's doing.
We can catch fish.
>> We can pick up what Lydia is
doing.
>> I know she's lazy, but
we need some big challengers.
>> Okay.
>> So we have a decision?
>> Lydia.
>> Well, I mean, is that what
everyone...
>> Yeah, yeah.
You know how it is, I love
Lydia, but, yeah, it has to be.
>> One of the things that you
can't do in this game is get
emotional, so, from now till
Tribal Council, I'm sure
there's going to be a lot of
thinking going on.
>> Lydia's name came up because
they think she's weaker because
she's older.
She's pulled her weight in
challenges.
She walked 11 miles with
everybody else.
The woman can do the work.
I told her, I said, "Lydia, it's
not looking good for you."
Because she needs to know.
>> Well, what's going on in camp
right now is not in my favor at
all.
I mean, I know my head is on the
chopping block tonight.
I know that for a fact.
Sounds like I'm going home.
I just don't think it's right.
I put my heart and soul into
every single challenge, and I
endeavored every single one of
them, you know?
So am I safe with you?
Because, you know, whatever you
guys want to do, I'll be there
for you.
>> I know that.
>> I'm not ready to go, Gary.
>> The main thing is that our
tribe votes somehow unified.
We don't want to have some crazy
vote that no one expected and
then us all be fractured at camp
and stuff.
The fact that we're going to
Tribal Council tonight sucks so
badly, but the hard reality of
the game is that that's what
happens.
>> JEFF: Behind each of you is a
torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch and
approach a flame.
Dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council because in this
game fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire you're
still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
So catch me up on the status of
this tribe.
Steph, what was the reaction
with you coming into this game
having already played it?
>> Actually they were really
welcoming.
I thought there might be a few
negative reactions.
I mean, I'm not an idiot.
They know that I played this
game.
I know how the game works.
But, um, we're one tribe and
it's important just to win
immunity and I feel that way and
I hope they feel that way, but
this game is a big bunch of lies
half the time.
>> JEFF: Jamie, what's the
problem with having somebody
like Steph out here?
>> She knows the game really
well.
She's always going to be a
threat, and she's tough.
She's not like a girl.
She's more like a boy.
>> JEFF: Who here of the women
doesn't play like a guy?
>> None of them play at the
level Stephenie does,
I don't think, in my opinion.
>> JEFF: Lydia, just looking
at you from the outside, you
could say maybe you're the least
equipped for this game.
It must run through your head a
little bit on this tribe if I'm
the least athletic, I could be
the first to go.
>> Actually it is, Jeff.
Sometimes, you know, you just
feel like deep down inside are
they really feeling that I can
endure this?
I think I've shown them, you
know, that I'm a person that
would never give up.
>> JEFF: Morgan, the vibe I'm
getting from you guys is this
really is one unified group,
but somebody is going home
tonight.
It's like it's an unspoken thing
that nobody is talking about.
What's your take on that?
>> I think that our tribe is
very unified because we've been
honest with each other up to
this point and so I think that
it's not an unspoken thing.
I think we all kind of know
what's going on, but somebody
has to go and I don't want to
say good-bye to anyone yet.
>> JEFF: Rafe, what are you
gonna base your vote on?
>> Tonight I'm basing my vote on
keeping this tribe unified.
You know, we have grown to
become something like a family
out here and going home tonight
without one of our members is
going to be a crushing blow that
hopefully we can move on from,
and I truly believe that we can.
>> JEFF: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Amy, you're up.
>> I hope to high heaven this
works.
I scrambled at the last minute.
>> Believe it or not, Lydia.
This is going to be one of the
hardest decisions that I make
while I'm out here.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Morgan.
Lydia.
One vote Lydia, one vote Morgan.
Morgan.
Two votes Morgan.
One vote Lydia.
Morgan.
That's three votes Morgan, one
vote Lydia.
Morgan.
Four votes Morgan.
One vote Lydia.
Second person voted out of
Survivor: Guatemala, Morgan.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Morgan, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, based on tonight's vote
I'm a little confused.
On the one hand, I do believe
you're unified and tonight was a
tough vote.
On the other hand, the person
voted out never saw it coming.
Grab your torches and head on
back to camp.
Good night.
>> Stay tuned for scenes from
our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor,
Nakum defies the crocodiles.
>> Everybody watches each
other's backs from these
crocodiles, we'll be all right.
>> Even though we can't see
them, there's probably hundreds
in this lake.
>> I've never felt more alive in
my entire life.
>> JEFF: And at Yaxha, Amy is in
trouble.
>> It's swollen.
>> Did you hear it snap?
>> Oh, yeah, snapped both sides.
>> You'll have to stick needles
in my eyeballs, I will not give
up.
>> Wow, I just didn't really see
that one coming at all.
I mean, I don't really know why
I got voted off.
I just feel really naive.
Either way, it was such an
amazing experience.
You know, I got to live in
Guatemala for almost a week and
I've done a lot of things
that I didn't think I
could do, so the experience of
it all was worth every second.