>> JEFF PROBST: We are off the
coast of Panama on a remote
island that will play a dramatic
role in the lives of our 16
survivors over the next 39 days.
This is Exile Island.
Each week, at least one survivor
will be banished here, separated
from their tribe-- they'll have
no idea what's going on back at
camp-- and they'll be forced to
live on their own until they
return to the game.
But there is a silver lining to
Exile Island: it's a mystery
that could help one of our
survivors win the million
dollars and the title of sole
survivor.
It's a twist like never before,
turning strategy on its head.
These 16 Americans have already
begun the adventure of a
lifetime.
They have been divided into four
tribes, each with four members.
They are strangers from
different walks of life, forced
to work together to create a new
society while battling the
elements and each other.
They must learn to adapt or
they'll be voted from the tribe.
In the end, only one will remain
to claim the million-dollar
prize.
39 days, 16 people, one...
survivor.
Captioning sponsored by
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
Come on in, guys.
Welcome to Survivor.
Cirie, what do you think about
the way you've been divided?
First reaction.
>> It looks like younger, older.
>> PROBST: Shane, is that what
it's sizing up to you?
>> Yeah, I mean, genders and
ages separated, the four of us.
I mean, it will be interesting.
I don't think this has ever
happened before.
>> PROBST: Shane's right.
For the first time ever, you
have been divided into four
tribes by age and gender:
Younger men versus younger women
versus the older men versus the
older women.
>> Uh... I thought I was young.
W-W-W-W-W-W--
(laughing): I'm on the wrong
team.
Why do they think I'm older?
Do I look older?
(older women laughing)
>> I would certainly prefer to
have some females on our team.
My personality, I can't help but
flirt with, you know, basically
any female I come into contact
with.
>> There was the young beefcake
crowd, of which I was the
charter member and president,
and then there was the Love Boat
crowd, which was the older men,
and there was the Golden Girls
and then there was the Spice
Girls.
It will be interesting to see
how things shake out.
>> PROBST: Let me tell you a
little bit about the island
you're on right now.
You will not be living here as
tribes, but over the next 39
days, many of you will be
spending some time out here
alone.
This is Exile Island.
Throughout this game, tribe
members will be banished to this
island, where you will have to
live with very meager supplies,
dealing with all the elements,
with nobody to watch your back.
And even worse, when you're on
Exile Island, you are not back
at your camp.
You are out of the loop and you
don't know what is going on.
Now I've got another surprise.
You're going to compete, right
now, in your first reward
challenge.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's get it on.
>> I was just pumped that we had
a challenge right off the bat.
I mean, that's my forte, that's
my thing.
I'm an athlete, you know, I'm
physical.
That's what I came here for.
>> PROBST: All right, each tribe
will choose one person to run
for them.
On my go, you will race to the
other end of the island, where
you will find a pile of skulls.
Taking one skull at a time,
smash it on a rock.
Inside, you'll find a tightly
wrapped ball of fabric.
Untie it.
You're looking for an amulet,
not a stone.
Once you find an amulet, race
back to the finish.
The first three tribe members
back with an amulet win, for
their tribe, fire in the form of
flint.
In addition, the losing tribe
will choose one person to stay
behind on Exile Island, right
off the bat.
>> (whistling): Wow.
>> PROBST: Big enough stakes?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: All right, I know you
don't know each other very well,
but you got to make a decision.
I'll give you a second to
strategize.
Who is going to run?
(all talking indistinctly)
>> PROBST: All right.
Older Women, who's going to run
the challenge?
>> Ruth-Marie.
>> PROBST: Older guys, who's it
going to be?
>> Terry.
>> PROBST: For the younger
women?
>> Danielle.
>> PROBST: How about for the
younger guys?
>> Austin.
>> PROBST: Austin, Danielle,
Terry, Ruth-Marie, come up to
the start.
>> Let's go, Terry.
>> Look for the amulet.
Look for the amulet.
>> PROBST: For reward in the
form of fire.
Survivors ready.
Go!
(all shouting)
Austin down already.
Gotta get those jitters out.
>> Let's go, Terry.
>> (whispering): I hope she can
pound it.
>> PROBST: Here comes somebody.
>> Let's go, Terry!
Yeah, Terry!
>> PROBST: Terry back first, for
the older guys.
Only two amulets remaining.
(whooping)
>> Yeah!
>> There he is.
>> Austin!
>> PROBST: Austin back with the
second amulet for the younger
guys.
>> My boy, that's my boy.
>> PROBST: Older women, younger
women, getting nervous?
Nobody wants to stay behind
here.
>> She's not a smasher.
>> God is gonna help her.
>> I just can't breathe until I
see her come up here.
>> Come on, Ruth, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on,
come on.
>> PROBST: Here comes the final
amulet.
I don't know who's got it.
>> Lord, please let it be
Ruth-Marie.
>> PROBST: Ruth-Marie back with
the final amulet for the older
women!
Older women, older men, younger
men all have amulets.
>> That's good, that's good,
that's great, you did it.
>> PROBST: Here she comes.
(applause)
For the young men, fire.
For the older guys, fire.
The older women-- Ruth-Marie.
>> Yay!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: For the younger
women, big disadvantage right
off the bat-- no fire, and the
worst news is you got to give me
a name now.
Who is going to stay behind at
Exile Island?
>> I'll stay.
>> Uh-uh.
>> You shouldn't have to.
>> I said, you know, "I lost the
challenge, I feel like I should
stay," and then the other girls
were like, "No, no, no, you
can't.
You just did the challenge."
You know, they were really cool
about it.
>> Should we, like, pick up
sticks or something?
Whoever gets the shortest?
>> Rock, paper, scissors?
>> That sounds great.
>> Can we do rock, paper,
scissors?
>> PROBST: You can do whatever
you want.
(talking indistinctly)
>> No one really wanted to make
a decision in our group.
The whole time I'm holding my
breath.
I'm thinking, "Please, God, I
don't want to start off Survivor
on the losing end."
>> One, two, three, hit-- ready?
>> All right, I'm here.
But, you know, I'm the one who
got stuck sitting on Exile
Island.
>> PROBST: Misty is sticking
behind.
>> I'm staying.
>> PROBST: Here's how it's going
to work.
You will stay here until the
first immunity challenge, at
which point, you will return
back to your tribe.
You will compete.
There's one other element to
Exile Island.
Hidden somewhere on this island
is an immunity idol.
>> Ooh-hoo.
>> PROBST: So while you're out
here trying to figure out how to
survive, you ought to be looking
for it.
If you find the idol, you can
share that information with
whoever you want.
You can keep it a secret.
It's up to you.
The important thing to remember
is that you can use it anytime,
up through the final four, but
once there are only three of you
remaining, the idol can be used
no more.
But here's the best part: you
can hold on to that idol until
after the votes have been
revealed at Tribal Council.
That means you could have enough
votes to get you voted out, you
hold up that idol, you are now
immune, and the person with the
next most votes goes home.
It is a huge shift in how this
game is played.
Along the way, you'll be given
clues as to the whereabouts of
that idol.
Younger Guys, get out of here.
Here's a map.
Let's go.
Older Guys, here's a map to your
beach.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Have fun.
>> All righty.
>> PROBST: Older Women.
(whooping)
Sally, Danielle, Courtney,
here's a map to your beach.
The boat is waiting to take you
there.
All right, Misty.
Tough way to start the game.
A few minutes in, you're
already left on your own.
Here's what you have on Exile
Island: one machete, one bucket
of water.
Water not going to do you a lot
of get good, 'cause you really
need to boil it before you drink
it, and you don't have fire.
You also have a lot of time to
think about why fate chose you
to be the first one out here,
which is also why immunity is
already so important.
And as for your first clue to
the whereabouts, I've already
given it to you.
Good luck.
See you at the immunity
challenge.
>> Nice work out there, buddy.
>> Uh-huh!
(yelling like Tarzan)
>> Where's the map?
Who's got the map?
>> I am the first person exiled
to Exile Island.
I definitely feel very
vulnerable.
I didn't expect this, this
soon, this early, so it came as
quite a shock.
Think, Misty, think.
Jeff did say there's an immunity
idol on the island, and he left
me with clues.
He said, "Why did fate leave
you behind?"
Behind me.
It seems to me like he was
trying to tell us that the
immunity idol was buried behind
us, where we were standing.
That was my guess, anyways.
Behind me.
I'm going to be definitely
searching for that immunity
idol.
(laughter)
(whooping)
>> Oh, we have a machete!
>> We walked up to the flag.
There was a pot and a machete.
The machete kind of scared me a
little bit.
I thought we might have to clear
an area to build a house or
something.
And clearing areas kind of
scares me, because when you
clear the area, the things that
used to live there come out, and
I'm not good with things.
>> And bless our team.
Bless everyone here...
>> Amen.
(laughter)
(whooping)
>> To finally be at your beach
where your tribe flag is, is
huge, and then, of course, we're
like, "Where are we going to
build a shelter?
Where are we going to build a
fire?
Oh, my gosh, we've got to do
this.
We only have two hours of
daylight."
You know? So we went straight
into work mode.
>> Ooh, that's pretty cool
stuff.
(howling)
>> ♪ Burn, baby, burn ♪
(whooping)
>> ♪ Disco inferno... ♪
Okay, here we go, kids.
More of that stuff.
Keep her going.
>> Good job!
(whooping)
>> Keep more sticks, more
sticks.
>> People, I think that was a
fire in record time, thank you.
>> I'm serious.
>> Yes!
Well, starting a fire was highly
successful for us.
Once you hit that flint, holy
schnikes, it's like a Fourth of
July fireworks parade.
Sparks were going everywhere.
♪ Kumbaya, my Lord,
Kumbaya... ♪
(grunts)
>> The Older Women are
performing very well.
Tina, who has the most
interesting background-- she's
actually a log roller-- she is a
very, very resourceful woman.
>> Water is ours!
>> And so with Tina stepping
forward into the leadership
position, I'm happy to step back
and be one of the worker bees.
(whimpering)
>> They're what?
You said something scared you.
>> There's a lot of scary stuff
around here, though.
>> I don't think Cirie has had
a lot of outdoor experience.
Heck, we went to gather leaves
to make a cushion for our bed
tonight, and she said she hates
leaves.
Did anyone tell her what show
she was going on?
I'm, like, thinking, "Leaves are
the least of your problem,
honey."
>> Oh, yeah, keep it to him.
>> Bam.
You better not strike out.
That would be a bum.
We haven't really prioritized
anything yet, and we got to
figure out how are we going to
get water, how are we going to
get fire, how are we going to
get shelter?
Put your left hand, like, an
inch over my left hand.
And they're all left hand?
Try to get it as close without
touching.
Now right hands.
Now, now, uh...
All right, we're going to leave
our hands here until you guys
start to feel something.
You tell me when you start to
feel a little bit of energy.
All right, so right now, I want
you guys just to think, right
now, what we're going to do.
We're going to make fire.
>> Okay.
>> All right?
Seriously, just take a second,
stop and think about that.
You guys feel anything in your
hands?
All right?
>> Aras, uh, has definitely...
He's got a lot of ideas.
Some of them are kind of
harebrained, out of left field,
like doing medication to get
fire.
>> All right, we'll make a...
>> (laughing): Machete?
>> It's over there.
>> It's right...
>> And it's, like, so grandiose.
Like, and you just want to go,
"Okay, how are you going to do
that?"
Like, we need to worry about
basics.
>> Use that power in the hand.
You got it.
>> Brace yourself.
>> Think about this thing and
catching it. Okay.
(clanging)
>> Oh, my hand.
>> Keep the faith.
Keep the faith, fellas.
>> I mean, is there something
we're just missing?
Like some component of
fire-building that everybody is
going to be, like, "Those four
jackasses!"?
>> No, we're getting sparks.
>> Our tribe's just hysterical.
I mean, we all established
within two hours of being here,
when we didn't have a fire
going, and hopelessly building
this pathetic shelter...
(clicks tongue)
We don't have a clue what we
are doing.
(laughs)
That's the shelter right there,
gentlemen.
>> Look at that.
>> (chuckling): Yeah.
>> Where's Bob Vila when you
need him?
>> That is the sorriest shelter
I think we could have
possibly come up with.
>> Possibly.
>> Got to be proud of it.
First night, you know?
We wouldn't want to peak the
first night.
>> Let's just hope it doesn't
rain.
Right now, it's not.
(birds calling)
>> Oh, this is kind of cool,
too, this little... story.
>> We could do a lean-to.
>> Yeah.
We could... and it's flat.
>> Well, there are so many
places.
I don't know.
We should keep looking.
Don't you think?
>> What would Misty like?
(laughing): What would...
>> It hasn't been the greatest
day for us.
We started off, like, you know,
underdogs.
Plus, you know, since we didn't
win the flint and, everyone else
did, we don't have fire, and
don't have water.
And we only have three of us,
so...
And none of us has ever made a
shelter before.
It's such a cool tree, huh?
It seems like we could do
something with this.
>> I don't know.
>> I'm-I'm not...
Are you feeling it?
>> No.
(laughter)
>> Nope... Next!
>> I'm just kidding.
>> We are so back-and-forth
about where to pick our shelter.
We were being women:
"Huh. Do you think this will
work?"
"I don't know.
What do you think?"
Is purple my color?"
Hmm.
Uh...
>> Do you want to keep walking?
Other options?
>> I-I'm happy walking, just
checking out where we're living,
just for fun.
>> All right, let's check it
out.
I started to get a little bit
frustrated with the whole, like,
where we should do the shelter.
If you see it and you like it,
don't even look any more,
because it's just a waste of
time at that point.
It's starting to get dark.
>> Oh, man!
How old this guy is.
Oh, man!
Dead, on this little beach.
Come on.
That's-That's really weird, huh?
Oh, we love you.
I thought it was really ironic
that the turtle, that
represents, like, mother and
goddess and, like, Native
American culture, and, that
like, this is the island where
three women, you know, are
living on.
It just to me, it just seemed
really significant.
I mean, they're just, like, such
a symbol.
Like, the turtle is Mother
Earth.
Even more specifically, North
America is called Turtle Island.
>> Courtney's kind of just so
out there.
She had all this symbolism for a
dead sea turtle.
To me, it's just a turtle.
I cannot fake that I'm, like,
deep into this.
>> Should we just...
>> I don't... I don't know.
I'm thinking about high tide,
just, like, rolling her back in
the ocean or something.
>> Rolling it back in the ocean?
>> Yeah.
>> I think Courtney...
she overdramatizes things, I
believe, which is not needed.
We need to, you know,
build a shelter, catch food,
build a fire.
>> Oh, my gosh.
It just freaks me out, man.
>> There's so much to do and so
little time to do it.
(birds singing)
(grunting)
>> All right, Bruce.
>> Some I already cut.
>> Awesome!
>> We're feeling really good
because we got our fire and
boiling water.
You see any other smoke on any
of the other islands?
>> Let's make a rally up into
the thing and get some really
dry wood, 'cause we're putting
wet wood on the deal.
>> Okay.
>> We're stoked.
We're Older Guys, and we're
into this, and we're doing the
Boy Scout thing right now.
That's the best-smelling
stinking fire I've seen in a
long time.
When people come over here, if
they do, they're going to see a
roaring fire, and they're going
to see some shrimp on the
barbie.
>> Can I trust you?
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
>> I'll never lie to you.
>> Okay.
>> And I expect you to never lie
to me.
>> I'll shake on that.
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> All right, we'll never lie to
each other.
>> No matter what.
>> All right.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
So...
>> That's awesome!
>> Yeah.
>> Well, I did do, do a little
white lie to you.
You know I am, you know, I'm an
American Airlines pilot...
>> Yeah.
>> ... but I-I didn't want
people knowing the military
thing.
Uh, yeah, I flew F-14s.
Aircraft carriers.
>> Terry's a great guy.
I found out he was a military
pilot, flew F-14s.
My background is that I retired
from NASA as an astronaut.
There are some similarities
between the expedition to space
and the expedition to a deserted
island.
The teamwork concept is very
much alive on this island.
>> By the way, I'm getting
chewed to death right now.
I don't know if they're in the
sand, but...
>> Let's get all these back
first, and don't waste a lot of
energy on one.
>> We're coming!
>> I already want to start
calling people out because
they're moronic.
>> Come on!
>> I'm with the older guys, so
the older guys, I don't really
fit in with them all that much,
and they just want to work all
the time, and I'm exhausted.
I haven't had a cigarette.
You know, I smoke three packs of
cigarettes a day for 20 years,
and I haven't had a cigarette in
like, 31 hours.
I mean, I'm just at the end of
my rope.
I'm fried.
Yo, man, we also got to stop
worrying about hurting people's
feelings at this point.
Like, we're here.
All four of us don't need to
get the water.
head to the path to find the
mud chute.
>> You're right.
>> Like... I'm, we're all
capable.
>> You betcha.
>> (whistles)
Do you have the machete?
I left it there.
>> What's Daffy Duck doing over
there?
What's he doing over there?
I am not in a good spot, man.
I've got to get through this
detox for sure, the cigarette
stuff.
It's...
I can't lash out at anybody.
I can't, I can't, I can't.
It is unbelievably hard.
And I've been here a day.
>> Woo-hoo!
(thunder rumbling)
>> Spending the night on Exile
Island was my worst nightmare.
I'm tired.
I'm hungry.
I'm really, really, really
thirsty.
Protein...
My tribe mates, the three of
them hopefully are doing better
than me, so they're strong for
our next immunity challenge.
But, uh, I definitely feel at a
huge disadvantage.
And I'm the first one voted off
should we not win.
So, I have been digging around,
because Jeff mentioned that
whoever finds the immunity idol
on Exile Island doesn't have to
tell anyone else.
Well, I think that's going to be
a huge advantage, and I
definitely want to use it.
So when I see my tribe mates at
the next immunity challenge,
I'll trick them into thinking
that I found the immunity idol.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Misty,
returning from her stay on Exile
Island.
>> How you guys doing?
>> How's it going?
>> PROBST: So, Misty, how's
Exile Island?
>> It's been lonely, but it has
its advantages.
>> PROBST: What advantages does
Exile Island have?
>> Well, you told us there was
an immunity idol in there, and
you told us where it was, so...
>> PROBST: So you spent a little
time looking for it.
>> Enough.
>> PROBST: Okay, well, in this
game, there is nothing more
powerful than what?
>> Immunity.
>> PROBST: Immunity.
This is what you're playing for.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: This is the immunity
idol.
There are three pieces to it
because at today's challenge,
three tribes will win immunity.
The losing tribe goes to Tribal
Council tonight, the first
person will be voted out of this
game.
Today's challenge is going to
test you physically.
It is also going to test you
mentally.
Here's how it works: all four
tribe members will start on the
dock.
On my "go," climb up and over a
barrier, swim out to your raft.
The raft is attached to a clip
underwater.
Once you've released the raft,
start paddling to shore.
You'll then race up the beach
where you have to solve a
brainteaser.
Your goal at the brainteaser is
to release a metal ring from the
rope.
Buried in the sand is a diagram
to help you.
Your dilemma is whether you
choose spend the time digging
that diagram up or solving the
puzzle on your own.
Once you release the metal ring,
you'll toss the ring out,
retrieve a grappling hook.
When you pull on the grappling
hook it drops a flag.
The first three tribes to drop
their flag win immunity.
Losing tribe, Tribal Council.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Swim out, we'll get
going.
Here we go, for immunity,
survivors ready!
Go!
Up and over, one at a time.
Everybody over.
Tina bringing it up for the
older women.
Now you've got to get down and
unhook those rafts.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Older men are the
first ones free.
Younger women right behind.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Older women cannot
get their rope released.
Younger guys having trouble
with their rope.
Older men having a little bit of
trouble paddling now.
Younger women staying calm.
The older women have released
their boat!
Younger guys still trying to get
that rope free.
Everybody following the lead of
the younger women.
Young guys in serious trouble.
Still cannot get it free.
They're swapping out.
Young women doing a good job.
Older men making progress.
Older women have it going on.
Younger guys have their rope
free.
All four tribes paddling to
shore.
>> Back, paddle back, backwards,
keep going backwards, you're
steering us.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Young women are first
back to the beach.
Moving on to the brainteaser.
Older men, right behind.
Trying to free that metal ring.
>> Here we go guys, let's do
this.
>> PROBST: Both tribes are
putting two people on the puzzle
and two people digging.
>> Here, we've got to get the
green rope out from here.
>> Let's see if we can get
through this.
>> PROBST: The older women are
now in it.
Younger women have found the
diagram.
Young guys in serious trouble.
Younger women making progress.
Melinda watching them.
While Cirie, Ruth-Marie, and
Tina dig.
Younger guys finally in.
>> Hold on.
>> PROBST: Young guys are moving
on to the brainteaser.
>> This around, this around.
>> PROBST: Tina, Ruth-Marie,
Cirie still looking for the
diagram.
Melinda trying to get a clue,
not digging.
That could be costly.
Young women have figured it out!
Young women are close.
That could do it.
Yank on it.
They've got it.
Younger women have immunity!
>> All right!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: 12 people still out
here.
You just don't want to be last.
>> I got it!
I got it!
>> PROBST: Dan has the clue for
the older men.
Younger men have the diagram.
The older women have it.
>> Lift both rigs up, both
rigs up.
>> Hold it, let me look, let me
look.
>> PROBST: Austin's bleeding.
Nick is bleeding, and they're
nowhere closer.
>> It's out, it's out, it's out!
>> PROBST: Older men have their
ring free.
Catch that hook, and you've got
immunity.
Bruce hooks it on his first
shot!
Older men win immunity!
They are safe from Tribal
Council.
Down to two tribes, one immunity
left.
Older women, younger guys.
>> This has to be straight.
>> ...And up and over it.
>> Look it, we're one twist
away.
>> Yeah, we've go it, we've got
it, we got it!
>> PROBST: The guys think
they're making some progress.
And they have.
The guys have solved it.
Older ladies, you better kick it
into gear.
This is about over.
>> But look at this though,
this is step number two.
>> PROBST: You got to toss it
over that grappling hook.
No.
Older women still in it.
>> Go, keeping going, keep
going.
>> PROBST: Down to two tribes.
Somebody going to Tribal
Council.
That could do it!
Younger men win immunity!
Older women going to Tribal
Council.
>> (cheering)
>> PROBST: Young guys, I don't
know how you pulled it out.
You got immunity.
Older guys, you've got immunity.
Because the young women finished
first, you get the bulk of the
idol.
Maybe it has a little more
spiritual power.
The older women came up short.
Tribal Council tonight, one of
the four of you going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Head on back to camp.
>> Tina, I'm thinking about
getting water.
>> Go ahead and get water.
>> Are you good with that?
>> Yeah. Water and wood in a
minute.
Well, we lost the challenge,
and, uh, someone has to go home
now... from our tribe.
I'm really nervous.
I don't feel like I'm the most
physically fit person on the
tribe.
I don't want to be the first one
to go home.
>> Well, we're going to go get
water...
>> (crying): I wrote this in the
sand for my son.
Charlie was killed in a car
accident just around four and a
half months ago.
And he was just 16 years old...
and he was my only child.
I am sad...
because I miss him.
But I would like to keep that to
myself for now.
So, I will come and talk to him
once in a while...
alone.
>> ...in any challenges?
And she said, "Well, no."
So, I mean...
>> I don't like to say that I'm
gunning for anyone, but I don't
want to go home.
So I'm going to try to get rid
of the lumberjack lady.
>> And I think Tina's starting
to aggravate her, just a little
bit.
Because she was like, "I mean, I
really like her, but she is kind
of loud."
>> Whoa!
That's a fish.
That thing is breathing.
Oh, my God.
Obviously, with the tide going
out, he must've got caught
here, and he's going to
become... (screams)
You little...
Ow!
He's a little son of a gun.
Big one!
>> Are you lying?
>> I'm not.
>> How did you catch a fish?
>> With my bare hands.
>> Oh, my...
>> Are you lying?
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Okay, now, um, how do we want
to cook it?
>> Don't we need to fry it?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, skewer it.
>> We can do it however you want
to do it.
>> There are a hundred reasons
to keep Tina.
She's a workhorse.
She caught a fish today.
I mean, honestly, there are a
gazillion reasons to keep her.
>> Let's go clean it.
>> We're going to fry him up.
>> I do think that Cirie's the
weak link right now.
>> Do you want to do it?
Go ahead and do it.
>> That's a big fish, you guys.
>> Slippery sucker.
I scaled the fish.
It's almost like everything that
I do is kind of like to ensure
to Ruth-Marie and Melinda that
we'll be okay without the
lumberjack lady.
And I hope it's working out.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch
and approach the flame,
dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual at
Tribal Council because, in this
game, fire represents your life:
as long as you have it, you're
still in the game; when your
fire's gone, so are you.
Take a seat.
Well, welcome to Tribal Council.
Not where you want to be.
Melinda, been out here three
days.
Tougher than you thought?
Less tough than you expected?
No, I would say that I'm
currently in Panamanian Hell,
right about now.
I mean, this is, by far, the
hardest thing that I've ever
done in my entire life.
And it's because it's
all-encompassing.
It's mentally, physically,
emotionally, spiritually,
I mean, that's why it's so
difficult.
You should try it.
>> PROBST: It that right, Cirie?
>> Absolutely.
I've never lived outdoors.
I've never even slept outdoors.
So, for the people at home that
are like me, on the couch, stay
on the couch.
(laughter)
>> I completely agree.
>> Seriously, it's totally crazy
to me.
But now that I'm here, I want to
do more.
>> PROBST: How you doing, Tina?
>> I think I'm doing well.
I think it's been exciting to be
out there.
And I knew it was going to be
very difficult, but, um, I'm
pretty confident in what I know
how to do.
And I've been living outdoors
all my life.
Ruth-Marie, that's got to be
a little comforting to have
somebody on your tribe who feels
very comfortable in the
outdoors.
>> Very much so.
It's been wonderful.
We have someone who had those
abilities and took charge.
And I think we did a good job
of saying, you know, let her
take the ball, run with it, and
we'll try to fill in the gaps.
>> PROBST: Cirie, it's starting
to sound like, in some ways,
Tina is leading you through
these first three days.
>> Yeah, you can say that.
She... kind of took that
position.
She did know how to start the
fire.
Um, she found the water.
>> PROBST: Those are two huge
things.
Starting fire and finding
the water are gigantic.
>> Well, if Tina didn't find the
water, I'm sure one of the three
of us could have found the
water; and I believe we can
start fire.
She just stepped up and started
doing things, so, I mean,
what do you do, break her arm,
don't do that, don't start
the fire?
Don't go fish?
>> TINA: Do you think these
other three are pulling their
weight?
>> Um, not as much as I would
like to.
I have a really huge work ethic.
But I feel like if I keep
saying, let's get more firewood,
let's go find a fishing spot,
they're going to look at me as
a bigger leader than I am, and
then my head's on the chopping
block.
So I just go out by myself and
work hard and have a good life.
>> PROBST: Melinda, any
disagreement on that?
>> Um, no offense to Tina,
because she really has been out
there working, but it's not like
she's out there working and the
three of us are taking a nap.
I mean, all four of us are
constantly doing something.
It's just that we might not be
doing the same thing Tina's
doing.
>> PROBST: Okay, well, three
days in, only four people;
sadly, there is very little room
to hide.
One of the four of you is about
to go home.
It is time to vote.
Melinda, you're up.
>> I wish I could've learned
more about you.
We just didn't click.
>> Somebody has to go, and your
fear of leaves was my biggest
factor because we have to go in
the leaves too.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Tina.
Cirie.
One vote Tina, one vote Cirie.
Tina.
Two votes Tina, one vote Cirie,
one vote left.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island.
Tina, would you bring my your
torch.
Tina, your tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Have fun.
>> PROBST: Well, you're only
three days in to what all of you
have agreed is already the
toughest thing you've ever done,
and yet, you vote out the one
person who could make your life
a little easier.
Be interesting to see how it
plays out.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
A twist on Exile Island raises
the stakes.
>> Ah...
>> PROBST: The pressure gets to
Shane.
>> There's no reason for me to
be doing this.
>> Shane wants to quit.
Let him quit.
>> PROBST: And the storm moves
in.
>> This place breeds bad luck.
(thunder crashes)
>> I think the girls made a huge
mistake, voting me out.
I hope they do terribly.
Working hard is what I do, and I
think it worked against me on
this one, but I would not have
been able to change a thing,
'cause that's just who I am.
That was really a great
experience.
I have no regrets.
I was just with the wrong girls.