>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, Bruce returned from
Exile Island...
>> We're going to filter water
through three T-shirts.
>> PROBST: ...and became a new
member of the Casaya tribe.
>> The tribe thought I was a
gift from Heaven.
>> He's on.
>> PROBST: At La Mina...
>> Oh, shoot!
Oh!
>> PROBST: ...things were
looking bleak.
>> If we could catch a few fish
a day, it would be a whole other
ball game.
>> PROBST: The reward challenge
was for camp comforts.
Tarp, lantern, some fuel.
And fire!
Terry once again dominated.
Terry makes an unbelievable
catch!
La Mina wins reward!
This time, the winners had to
send someone from the losing
tribe to Exile Island.
Who are you sending?
>> Bruce.
We're sending him back.
>> PROBST: And Bruce was
banished for the second time in
a row.
>> Those guys are playing for
keeps, huh?
>> PROBST: La Mina's new tarp
kept them warm and dry, but
Bruce didn't fare so well.
At Casaya, Shane, Courtney,
Aras and Danielle's alliance
was strained.
>> You're out of your mind, man.
You are crazy.
>> These are the people that you
guys decided to align with.
How stupid is that?
>> I want one!
This one!
I just want mine!
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Bruce rejoined his
tribe for one of the most brutal
challenges yet, and Casaya
battled their way to victory.
(cheering)
Back at La Mina, Dan and Terry
schemed with Austin and Nick.
>> Dan and I, as soon as we got
the two younger guys, we got on
them quickly, and the plan at
Tribal Council tonight is to
vote off Misty.
>> PROBST: But Misty and Sally
had other plans.
>> Ruth Marie is pretty weak
right now.
>> Could you vote for Ruth
Marie?
>> PROBST: So Austin and Nick
had a tough choice to make.
>> We could either go with Sally
and Misty or Dan and Terry.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
the men came together...
>> Tonight, I'm going with the
group.
>> PROBST: ...and Misty became
the third person voted out.
Misty, the tribe has spoken.
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> There you go.
That's a freakin' flame.
>> Last night, we went to Tribal
Council and Misty was voted out,
and the guys had said that the
vote was going to be for Ruth
Marie, so it seems I was the odd
woman out and it kind of
isolated me from the rest of the
group.
Is there anything that you guys
need?
>> We're going to need some
wood.
>> There are some big boys in
that camp that are calling a lot
of the shots, and all I can do
right now is keep working hard
and prove myself valuable.
>> We need to talk a little bit.
>> All right.
>> Me and Terry and Nick and
Austin and you.
>> Thank you.
>> What do you think?
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
I've been thinking a lot about
who should be the fifth person
to take to the merge, and I
thought that Ruth Marie was the
one to go with.
>> Well, I'm totally
appreciative and I'm loyal.
>> Yeah, well, that's why you're
here.
I don't think Sally feels like a
part of this team, and I think
when a merge comes, Sally will
drop us like a stone, but with
Ruth Marie, I think she'll stay
with that group of five all the
way to the end.
>> All right.
We have the numbers here.
We got the four guys and stuff,
and we're all four strong guys.
>> Yeah, but when the tribes
merge, we need a fifth.
>> Right.
>> And Dan suggested that it
would be Ruth Marie.
>> You know what?
That's fine, that's fine.
We've got a really strong
alliance of the four guys and
kind of a fifth right now is
Ruth Marie.
>> I'm pretty confident with the
alliance that we have.
Everybody has shaken hands on it
and looked each other in the
eye, so I have a good feeling
that we have an alliance that
will make it to the merge.
>> That one.
I got a good one.
>> There are some big ones
there.
>> The sun comes out.
Shane, myself and Bruce went
and got snails.
We got pounds of snails.
>> Ready to go back in?
>> As we're walking back, we
look over and we see Courtney,
and the problem is that I think
some people on this tribe don't
realize exactly what being on an
island by yourself means.
We haven't eaten today yet.
>> Hello, ladies.
>> You guys boil a pot of snails
already?
>> Where's "D" at?
>> How is the fish?
Sleeping.
How is the fish?
>> We got to talk about...
>> Work.
>> ...effort at camp.
>> We came back with two bags of
snails and the fire was like...
And nothing was ready, and Shane
and Aras, they'd just had it.
>> Yo, Bob, Danielle.
>> What?
>> We all want to have a talk
about camp responsibilities.
We can't be out catching food
for a whole day and then the
onus of fire is on us.
>> Honestly, that kills me to
hear that because I'm constantly
working, so I don't know.
I think the whole question is
kind of stupid.
>> Shane, Courtney and
Danielle-- I gave those people
my word in the alliance, but if
I had my druthers, I wouldn't
want to be in the alliance with
Courtney.
I would almost lose it on
purpose to get Courtney voted
off because she just gets on my
nerves.
>> When we're eating, can we
agree not to argue?
>> I didn't do anything.
>> No arguing during dinner.
>> Things were planned and
alliances were made, and I was
told that I would be the one to
go after Melinda, but it's just
constant, constant drama.
I love it, love it, love it.
Yes!
So my strategy right now is kind
of just continue to work like
I've been working and stay out
of the drama.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Casaya, getting your first look
at the new La Mina tribe.
Misty voted out last Tribal
Council.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Here's how it works:
each tribe has six floating
puzzle pieces.
On my "go," one tribe member at
a time will swim out, dive down,
unclip a puzzle piece, and bring
it back to the puzzle frame.
Once you have the piece in the
puzzle frame, the next person
goes out.
Once you've collected all six of
the pieces you need, you can
start assembling the puzzle by
matching the corresponding
symbols on each side of every
piece of the puzzle.
The first tribe to get it
together correctly wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Today you are playing
for a full-on Survivor bathroom.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Towels, loofah, some
soap, plenty of Charmin.
>> That's great.
>> PROBST: Hopefully help take
the edge off.
You'll have a sink, you'll have
a toilet seat, you'll have a
bush shower.
You'll have five gallons of
fresh water.
"Casa de Charmin" will be
delivered to the camp who wins
this challenge.
For the losers, one person
will be sent from here to Exile
Island where they will remain
until the next immunity
challenge.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Let's swim out, we'll
get started.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Sally and Bobby in the water.
Looking for six pieces.
Bobby at the first piece.
Sally going for the first piece.
Bobby goes down to unclip.
Sally has hers.
Bobby has his.
La Mina pulling ahead.
The hard part of this is getting
the muscle to get it in the
ring.
>> There you go, there you go,
come on.
>> PROBST: You got to muscle it
up and inside that puzzle ring.
>> Legs, legs, legs!
>> PROBST: Sally with a great
strategy.
>> Pull it, Bob!
>> PROBST: Bobby can't get it in
the ring.
You got to get it in the ring
before you can move on.
Go, La Mina!
Bobby losing time for Casaya.
Go, Casaya!
Bruce in the water.
Dan goes down to unclip.
>> You got it, Bruce!
>> PROBST: Dan has his
unclipped.
>> Come on, Dan!
>> PROBST: Dan back with the
second piece for La Mina.
Bruce has a piece untied.
He's coming back.
>> Let's go, Bruce.
Come on, now, Bruce.
>> PROBST: Got to get it in the
ring.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Ruth Marie in the
water.
Bruce back with the second piece
for Casaya.
Danielle in the water.
Ruth Marie coming back with the
third piece for La Mina.
Danielle going out wide.
>> Ruthie, good job.
>> PROBST: Ruth Marie's got to
get that in the puzzle ring.
>> Good job, good job.
>> PROBST: Got to get it all the
way in.
Danielle making up a lot of time
for Casaya.
Got to get it all the way, La
Mina.
Go, La Mina!
Nick in the water for La Mina.
Shane, go for Casaya!
We're neck and neck.
Both tribes with three pieces.
Nick, back quickly with a piece.
Shane, back quickly with a piece
for Casaya.
We're neck-and-neck-- Nick and
Shane.
Gotta get it inside the puzzle.
Go, La Mina.
Austin in the water for La Mina.
Shane's gotta get it in, the
last bit.
Courtney in the water for
Casaya.
La Mina with a bit of lead now.
Austin tangled up, losing time.
Courtney made up some time.
We're neck and neck again.
Austin back with the fifth piece
for La Mina.
Courtney back with the fifth
piece for Casaya.
Can't start solving the puzzle
until all six pieces are in.
Gotta get it in, Austin.
You're not in.
Austin thought he had it.
Go, Casaya.
Austin lost some time for La
Mina.
Terry in for La Mina.
Both tribes looking for their
last pieces.
Aras goes down to unclip.
Terry goes down for the final
piece for La Mina.
Terry coming back with the final
Aras coming back with the final
piece for Casaya.
Terry's put La Mina back in the
lead.
Once you have the last piece in,
then you start solving it.
Terry with the sixth piece for
La Mina.
Start solving the puzzle.
Aras, get it in there.
Start solving Casaya.
Both tribes solving the puzzle.
Reward at stake.
The loser-- sending somebody to
Exile Island.
Each piece will match up with a
corresponding symbol on every
side.
>> Bring that one right around
here.
>> PROBST: Dan and Sally trying
to lead together.
Casaya kind of doing it on their
own.
Casaya very close.
Casaya wins reward!
(cheering)
Casaya, congratulations.
You have a big decision to make.
Somebody from La Mina is going
to be sent to Exile Island.
Shane, who's it gonna be?
>> Terry.
>> PROBST: Terry, going to Exile
Island.
>> PROBST: Bring in the boat.
Casaya, your reward will be
waiting for you at camp.
Enjoy it.
♪ ♪
>> How many days have we been
gone?
>> We lost the reward challenge
today, and Casaya got to decide
who would go to Exile Island.
They chose Terry, which we all
knew they would, because he's
our leader.
>> When Terry comes back, he's
going to be proud at the way his
camp looks.
We're gonna pull this together.
You know, it's tough-- morale is
down after losing, but we are
gonna use this to start changing
this from a place that we're
just barely getting by on, to a
place we're gonna live for
awhile.
>> I think we need to eat.
Eat early before it rains.
>> I think we might all take a
nap.
Sun's up right now.
>> Well, you can take a nap, but
I'm afraid I'm gonna miss
another meal.
(all talking at once)
>> With Terry not being here,
you just don't have that person
who just seems like they're
completely in charge.
He makes everything just work in
such an orderly fashion.
Without him, it seems as if we
have people all coming up with
different ideas.
I miss him.
I'm ready for him to come back.
>> Good job, everybody.
We all worked hard.
>> Oh, look at the bathroom.
>> Check it out.
>> It has a shower curtain.
>> No way.
>> Casa de Charmin is awesome.
>> It's beautiful.
>> What we won in the reward
challenge was a bathroom with a
shower, toilet paper and a
toilet seat.
>> Nice.
Man, look at all that toilet
paper up there.
>> We've got five gallons of
water, a sink bowl, three bars
of soap, a bunch of towels, a
back scrubber...
Great.
>> You guys want to talk about
uses for what we just won?
>> Yeah.
>> My vote is to use the
bathroom for firewood, just
keeping things dry.
Towels, firewood.
>> Anyone mind if I break in the
dumpster?
I got a deuce to drop.
>> We should use the
bathroom to keep the wood dry.
>> The rocket scientist, brain
trust that we have decided
immediately that the first thing
we were gonna do with our fresh,
new, brand-new toilet was store
wood in it.
I was like... all right, I'm
gonna go in here and take a dump
before you start storing wood in
the toilet.
>> He's dropping a deuce?
>> Yeah, I mean, it's got all
the clean towels and everything
in there.
Bobby just frustrates me, all
day.
He's not a gentleman.
I can't stand the fact that he's
not a gentleman.
I just can't deal with people
like that.
>> I don't think that was a wise
decision.
>> How was it?
>> Feeling about ten pounds
lighter.
Like a whole new man.
>> Let's enjoy our victory,
guys-- two in a row.
>> Terry's gone for two days and
he's gonna be undernourished, no
water.
Coming back for the immunity
challenge, he's gonna be weak.
We got 'em right where we want
'em, you know?
Which is their leader hurt, and
the rest of the tribe underfed.
Terry's in hell.
>> The hidden immunity idol.
"It's not found here but is
hidden beneath a rock."
"Clue two, day four.
It is up above the tide line."
"Clue three, day seven.
It is buried underground.
"Clue one, day one.
You also have a lot of time to
think about why fate chose you
to be here...
which is also "why" immunity is
already so important."
Why?
"It is hidden beneath a rock."
I'm not hitting any roots.
(clunking)
Yeah, that's the end.
Woo-hoo.
Ah, totally.
"Break the bottle and retrieve
the hidden talisman."
The talisman, beautiful.
"This talisman can be used to
keep you safe from the vote at
Tribal Council, up to and
through the final four."
"Up to and through the final
four."
All right!
(owl screeches)
This makes the whole trip out
here worthwhile.
I mean, they ended up doing me a
big favor.
That immunity idol in my back
pocket is definitely my ace in
the hole.
>> Such a bummer, huh?
Should we just start a new fire
pit somewhere else?
>> Our fire was out, dead.
So Aras and Shane decided that
we should move the fire pit
closer to the shelter.
>> Right here, man.
>> I feel like if Shane pushes
or something, it happens.
Or if I push for something, it
happens.
And Cirie works her butt off.
But there's a lot of people on
this tribe who are just kind of
like... eh.
>> An aversion to working.
>> Oh, okay, that's, that's
nice.
>> No, I'm just telling you, I
think everyone has the same
opinion.
>> Bobby, too, huh?
He does a lot.
He sleeps.
>> Right now, we're not talking
about Bobby.
I'm talking about you.
You don't do a lot while you're
here.
>> If you're gonna be a ...
about it, then whatever.
Shane, sometimes, he has a
bad attitude.
I mean, I was a captain in
sports, and you just... you
don't get like that-- like
demeaning you, you know.
Why, why do you want to help
them?
>> Guys, am I the only one who
thinks that?
>> What's going on?
>> That Danielle doesn't work
very hard?
>> I agree with Shane, Danielle.
To be perfectly honest.
>> What do you do?
Do you get water?
You ever gotten water?
Alls you do is ask people to get
fire for you so you can do the
fire.
That's all you do.
>> What do I do?
>> That's all you do!
>> I hunt every day...
>> I don't know if you guys
catch food...
>> I go and get as much wood as
you do...
>> I get wood, I get the water,
I help you guys get snails.
What the... What are you talking
about?
>> Danielle, we're not gonna
have this discussion...
>> No, we are gonna have this
discussion because you just made
me feel like I don't do
anything.
>> Are you worried about what
people think of you?
>> I'm worried about what
everyone thinks about me here,
and for you to say it like
that...
>> And everybody here won't tell
you because they're afraid to
tell you the truth!
>> Why are they afraid to tell
me...
>> I don't know!
Cirie, you think she works hard?
>> That should've been my cue...
to start walking.
But no, uh-uh, I had to stand
right there.
>> I think I contribute.
>> What?
>> ...not as hard as everyone
else.
>> Not as hard as everyone else.
>> She does stuff...
>> Stuff.
>> ...but some people just do
more.
>> All right.
>> The Danielle-Shane-and-
Courtney-Aras foursome is like
some psychotic joke, and it
seems to be unraveling little by
little.
Yay.
>> I'm so weak now, man.
>> When in your life do you not
eat something all day long?
>> I know, it's miserable.
>> I'm starving.
It's day 11, and we really
haven't had anything to eat.
>> Oh, my God!
Look at 'em!
>> He's been out there a long
time.
>> How can it be so hard to
catch fish?
>> Aren't you hungry?
>> I am hungry, yeah.
>> You should eat more.
>> Yeah, you got to eat
something.
>> That's great.
(sighs)
We really suck at fishing.
We're catching no fish.
We haven't eaten.
I figure we've got about three
more days before the entire
tribe can't get out of bed.
So we're in pretty dire straits
right now.
>> That sucks.
>> Today is the roughest day so
far, plus with Super Terry
being gone...
That stupid fire.
We cannot get that thing going
without a dogfight.
(blowing)
>> You've got to be kidding me.
>> It's raining, guys.
>> What do we do now?
>> We really didn't need that.
>> Let's just gather the stuff
up.
>> The guys are really
struggling today.
And I don't know how much game
these people have left in them.
>> I'm tired, man.
>> I'm just wrecked.
>> It's just so frustrating
'cause it's my butt on the
line.
And if we lose another immunity
challenge, I'm going home.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Terry,
returning from Exile Island.
>> There he is.
>> PROBST: Welcome back.
(applause)
Long two days out there?
>> Peaceful two days.
>> PROBST: The good side to
Exile Island is the hidden
immunity idol.
Here's what we know: only three
people have been to Exile
Island.
Misty was voted out.
She obviously didn't have it.
Bruce and Terry are the only
two people who have been there.
They may have found it.
It may still be up for grabs.
Certainly a valuable item
either way.
You guys ready to get to
today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Shane.
Thank you.
Immunity, it's back up for
grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
you're going to have to test
your balance, your teamwork,
and your patience.
Here's how it works: one person
will begin seated on a chair,
which is attached to a pulley.
Another person will be situated
directly above them in a crow's
nest where an empty water drum
hangs.
The other four remaining tribe
members will be tied together
in pairs.
You'll race across a balance
beam carrying buckets.
Once you reach the water, dip
your bucket in, get water, and
race back.
You'll then empty your water
into a larger pail.
The person in the crow's nest
will pull that pail up, empty
the water into the drum.
As the drum takes on water, it
will lower.
The person in the chair will
rise until they're high enough
to pull the pin, releasing the
tribe flag.
First tribe to release their
flag wins immunity, is safe
from Tribal Council.
Losers, another person will be
going home.
One big rule: if you fall off
the balance beam at any point,
you lose all of your water in
your buckets and go back to the
start.
Casaya, you have one extra
member.
You're sitting somebody out.
You cannot sit out the same
person in back-to-back
challenges.
>> Bob-dog.
>> PROBST: Bob-dog sitting
this one out?
All right.
Give you a minute to strategize
and we'll go.
All right, pairs for Casaya
are Shane and Courtney, Bruce
and Aras.
For La Mina, Sally and Austin,
Dan and Terry.
Here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Let's go, come on, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
>> PROBST: Both tribes on the
course working together well.
Sally and Austin making quick
work of this course.
Dan and Terry, working slowly
but effectively.
Shane and Courtney doing well.
Aras and Bruce taking their
time.
Sally and Austin, going to be
first off the beam.
Shane and Courtney in the water.
Have to figure out how to
navigate.
Only one tribe at a time on
this course.
>> You got it, guys.
>> PROBST: Shane and Courtney
waiting on Aras and Bruce.
Sally and Austin waiting on Dan
and Terry.
Dan having a little trouble.
>> Way to go, Dan!
Looking great!
>> Take it slow, take it slow.
>> Nice!
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: They're through.
Shane and Courtney back on the
course.
Sally and Austin back on the
Shane and Courtney have the
right of way.
>> Come on, Shane and Courtney,
let's go.
>> PROBST: Shane and Courtney
are going to be first back with
water.
>> Take it slow.
>> PROBST: Austin and Sally
right behind.
Put the water in the pail.
Once it's full, people in the
catbird, pull it up.
>> Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Cirie pulling up the
first bucket for Casaya.
Sally and Austin working well
together.
No trouble.
Nick pulling up the first
bucket for La Mina.
Aras and Bruce coming back with
water.
Dan and Terry have full buckets
of water.
We're neck and neck.
>> Come on, Dan!
You're the man, baby!
>> PROBST: Both tribes across
with more water.
Get it in the pail and pull it
up.
Sally and Austin get the right
of way this time.
>> Slow and steady, fellas.
>> PROBST: The quicker you get
the water into your pail, the
faster you're back out on the
course.
Dan and Terry, more water for
La Mina.
Get it in the pail and pull it
up.
Sally and Austin coming back
with water.
Shane and Courtney, they've
filled up their buckets.
They're coming back.
Dan having a little trouble.
Dan falls off.
Dan and Terry have to go back
to the start.
>> We're coming!
We're coming!
>> PROBST: That wasted a lot of
time for La Mina.
Shane and Courtney waiting on
Aras and Bruce.
>> Good work together, guys.
>> PROBST: Casaya has been very
solid.
La Mina back with more water.
And very close.
A little wobbly.
Nick careful not to spill a
drop.
Shane and Courtney back with
more water for Casaya.
Sally running across the beam.
>> Come on, Cirie, you got it.
Drop that back down.
>> PROBST: Aras and Bruce
filling up that pail.
Both tribes very close.
Immunity at stake.
Aras and Bruce back on the
course.
Dan and Terry running to get
water.
Austin and Sally running to get
Shane and Courtney heading out
for more water.
>> Come on, guys.
You got it.
>> PROBST: Keep moving!
Both tribes, keep moving.
>> Sally and Austin go first.
>> PROBST: Shane and Courtney
have more water heading back.
It's coming down to the wire.
Aras and Bruce have to get off
the course.
Will this be enough water?
Right of way goes to Sally and
Austin.
They're flying over this course.
Sally and Austin with a little
bit of a lead over Shane and
Courtney.
Will it be enough water?
Got to get it into that pail and
get it up into the drum.
>> Come on, come on, come on!
>> Go fast!
>> PROBST: We are very even.
You're getting close to having
enough water.
Austin pouring carefully.
Casaya gets their water in more
quickly.
Will this be enough?
It could be a race to the
finish!
Cirie dumps it.
It might be.
>> Come on!
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: La Mina's bucket is
full.
Who's going to get there first?
(cheering)
Casaya wins immunity!
(cheers and applause)
>> Way to work, man!
>> PROBST: Another evenly
matched challenge, but Casaya
continues their winning streak.
Congratulations.
La Mina, a return visit to
Tribal Council.
Somebody else going home.
You have the afternoon to
figure out who that's going to
be.
Get your stuff, head on back,
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> The fire.
>> Where do you want to build
it, up there?
>> Up there.
>> We were absolutely thrilled
to see Terry, and it was very
comforting to have somebody
come in and just take over
again.
It was fabulous.
>> Did they give you one clue
or did they give you everybody's
clue up till now?
>> Everybody's clue up till now.
Where to try to find it and
everything.
It was a bear.
>> How much time did you spend
looking?
>> Maybe I looked, uh, two hours
or something.
>> We talked about my two days
on Exile Island, but nobody has
directly asked me, "Did you
find the idol?"
So my intention is to hide the
immunity idol.
I want to have that in my back
pocket in case I need it down
the road.
>> I hate losing, guys.
>> I know we did our best.
>> We lost the immunity
challenge.
That sends us to Tribal Council.
Not happy about going there
tonight.
I don't think there's any way
around the fact that we're
going to be voting out Sally.
>> All right, here's the deal.
I just want to tell you,
whatever happens tonight, I
respect you both.
I know there's an alliance, but
I do have a lot of game left in
me.
>> We know you do.
>> And I'd like to be here
tomorrow, so that's all I have
to say about that.
I went up to Terry and just
said, "You know, I proved
myself at the challenge today,
and I feel like I still deserve
to be here."
All right, well, we're going to
go get some water.
Who knows if that will sway
anything?
Terry calls the shots around
here, and if he doesn't think
I'm worth keeping around, then
I'm gone tonight.
>> I know.
I'm thinking about our tribe
here, man, because before we
know it, it's going to be down
to the four of us.
We don't want to go in four
people at the merge.
We're going to get picked off
one by one, you first.
You've got the biggest target on
your back of anybody on this
whole beach.
>> Shane's a good athlete.
He's better than I thought he
was.
>> Yeah, there's definitely a
lot more than meets the eye with
the Shane dog.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Oh.
But here's the thing.
You never promised Ruth Marie,
I never promised her.
Nor did Nick.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yeah, Dan just gave his word,
shook his hand.
We never made that pact with
her.
>> Austin came up to me and
pitched voting off Ruth Marie
instead of Sally.
Ruth Marie was given a promise
and a handshake by Dan alone,
but since then, some things have
changed.
My goal was to come into the
merge with numbers, and it's not
looking good right now.
>> What do you think?
>> Okay.
>> You are?
>> Cool.
I thought it was going to take
a water-into-wine type of
miracle to pull Terry into
keeping Sally as our fifth.
Apparently, I got some Jesus of
Nazareth-like powers myself.
>> I know how you gave Ruth
Marie a handshake, but neither
one of us did.
I know you made a promise, and
your word is your bond, and, uh,
that's fine.
But I'm looking at getting us
four intact to the merge, and,
uh, the strongest way possible
is to have the strongest player,
I think, which is Sally.
>> I just can't believe how
quickly it falls apart.
Austin and Terry-- they're
saying now, "You had the
handshake with Ruth, so it's
okay for us to back out."
But we had an understanding to
go to the final five, and to
change horses midstream is a big
mistake.
It's crazy.
Be aware.
If we take out Ruth tonight,
we're down to four anyway,
'cause Sally is going to jump
ship.
I don't care what she says.
She'll say anything right now.
>> Dude, I know she'll stay with
us.
She wants to be in this alliance
so bad, she...
>> Well, that's my thing.
She wants to be in it so bad...
>> I...
>> ...she'll do whatever.
Whereas Ruth would die on her
sword before she would give up
her word.
I think Sally would say, "It's
a game.
I'm playing the game.
I'm switching around."
>> There's a lot of strategy
discussion amongst the tribe
right now.
Terry-- he tried to get real
technical about it, said it was
really just Dan's promise to
Ruth Marie, and it's kind of
like an easy, hollow
rationalization.
I feel bad the way it's turned.
Ruth Marie is part of the five
of us, so I just...
I don't want to go back on that.
>> Oh, look, they're all in
here.
Look.
>> Yeah.
>> It's a shame to pack up
my stuff and leave here with so
much left to offer this tribe.
It still could change.
I know there's some talking
going on.
It's like the almighty men are
upstairs plotting, and us little
woman are just down here going,
"I wonder what they're going to
do."
>> Tell you what.
We're going to eat every
stinking one of them.
>> I'm never going to be
confident in Tribal Council, but
I'm not walking around paranoid.
I don't think it's me tonight.
So Sally will be going home,
unless something turns that I
don't know about.
>> This is going to be a Tribal
Council for the books right
here.
Dan is campaigning hard for Ruth
Marie.
I'm pulling for Sally.
So tonight's vote is completely
still up in the air.
We don't know what's going to
happen.
(insects chirring)
>> PROBST: Welcome back to
Tribal Council.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Terry, tell me about
Exile Island.
Describe it to somebody who has
never been there.
>> Uh, basically, you're there
with a barrel of untreated
water, a flint and a machete.
No sleeping quarters.
You've got to try to go gather
your own food, and that's it.
It's a unique experience, but I
don't necessarily want to go
back there.
>> PROBST: Sally, did anybody
question him about the immunity
idol?
>> We talked about it a little
bit.
You know, he kind of said, "I
spent a couple of hours looking
for it."
He didn't give anything away,
but he didn't give any
indication to let us know that
he found it, either.
>> PROBST: Austin, what did you
miss about Terry when he was
gone?
>> The best thing about having
Terry around is he's a natural
leader.
When he was gone, the rest of us
were kind of floundering.
It's not like we're all inept
people, but it's nice to have
somebody kind of take charge and
say, "Hey, you guys be doing
this," type of thing.
So, it's nice to have him back.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
individual performance today in
the challenge.
Sally, you dominated.
>> No matter what the challenge
is, whether it's immunity or
whatever, I'm going to give it
everything I have.
My best days out here are the
days where we compete.
And there was no way I was
falling off that thing, and I
went as fast as I could, so...
>> PROBST: Austin, what mistake
have you made in the 11 days?
>> Just in the challenge today.
The bottom line was, both tribes
had ample water to finish it
off.
Had I known that that was the
amount that was going to put us
over the edge, I wouldn't have
been pouring like my
grandmother.
You know, I was over there just
taking my sweet, precious time
with it.
Meanwhile, they polish it off,
and they win the thing.
So, you know, I'll take the
blame for that.
>> PROBST: Ruth Marie, what's
holding you back in this tribe?
>> Um, I think I'm small in
stature, and I'm twice as old
as the other women.
>> PROBST: But you've been out
here 11 days.
Do you feel like you've proven
yourself?
>> I do.
>> PROBST: Let's go back to the
last Tribal Council.
Sally, you're one big happy
tribe, and then Misty goes.
Never saw it coming.
Surprised?
>> Oh, yeah, I was very
surprised.
I was the only one who voted
with Misty.
I mean, I was the only one who
didn't know what was going on,
so clearly, I was surprised.
>> PROBST: Do you think you know
what's going on tonight?
>> You know, it's hard to say.
I think everybody here is great,
and I want to be here tomorrow,
and I want to wake up tomorrow
in that bamboo bed, but so does
everybody else, so...
>> PROBST: Ruth Marie, if it's
you, what will this tribe miss
tomorrow?
>> I don't know that they will
miss it tomorrow, but I am just
steady, steady, steady, and get
better as the game goes on.
And I am an extremely loyal
person.
And that may show up down the
road.
>> PROBST: Okay, before we get
to the vote, Terry, you're the
only person who has been to
Exile Island.
You may or may not have found
the idol.
If you need to, you'll let me
know after the vote.
It is time to vote.
Austin, you're up.
>> It's probably going to be you
or me tonight, girl, so I'll
miss you.
>> Sally, I adore you, but I'm
voting my alliance.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Ruthie.
Sally.
Ruth.
Two votes Ruth, one vote Sally.
Sally.
We're tied-- two votes Sally,
two votes Ruth.
That's three votes Ruthie.
Two votes Sally.
One vote left.
Fourth person voted out of the
Survivor: Exile Island-- Ruth
Marie.
You need to bring me your torch.
Ruth Marie, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, in spite of the fact that
you've lost two tribe members in
a row, you still seem positive,
and that more than anything can
help you to turn this game
around.
Grab your torches.
Back to camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
...stomach trouble threatens La
Mina.
>> I just felt wrecked.
>> PROBST: Bruce's Zen garden is
invaded by Courtney.
>> We have the whole beach, and
she picks this spot.
I'd rather be on Exile Island
than be around Courtney.
(thunder rumbling)
>> PROBST: And Casaya's spark is
snuffed out.
>> This is a nightmare.
>> I think my tribe
underestimated the endurance
that I have.
I'm not upset about their
decision.
It's a game.
It's fun.
There are lots of twists and
turns, but when you go through
an experience like this, it
humbles you a little bit.
So, Sally, Dan, Terry, Austin,
and Nick, I just wish them good
luck.