>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: 16 castaways began
their adventure as four tribes.
This is Exile Island.
Throughout this game, tribe
members will be banished to
this island.
The tribes immediately faced
off in their first reward
challenge.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's get it on.
>> PROBST: The losing tribe will
choose one person to stay behind
on Exile Island right off the
bat.
In a race to find three amulets,
the older men, the younger men,
and the older women were all
winners.
The young women finished last
and chose Misty to stay behind.
>> All right, I'm here.
>> PROBST: And a secret of Exile
Island was revealed.
Hidden somewhere on this island
is an immunity idol.
Along the way, you'll be given
clues as to the whereabouts of
that idol.
At the older women's camp, Tina
emerged as a natural leader.
>> Okay, here we go, kids.
Starting a fire was highly
successful.
>> PROBST: The young men
floundered.
>> That is the sorriest shelter
I think we could have possibly
come up with.
>> PROBST: And the younger women
struggled with indecision.
>> Are you feeling it?
>> Next.
>> I started to get a little
bit frustrated with the whole,
like, where we should do the
shelter.
>> PROBST: The older men thrived
>> That's the best-smelling
stinking fire I've seen in a
long time.
>> PROBST: And Dan, the
astronaut, bonded with Terry,
the fighter pilot.
>> I'll shake on that.
>> PROBST: But Shane was on
edge.
>> I smoke three packs of
cigarettes a day, and I haven't
had a cigarette in, like, 31
hours.
It is unbelievably hard.
>> PROBST: Alone on Exile
Island, Misty toughed it out...
>> I'm hungry.
I'm really, really, really
thirsty.
>> PROBST: ...and made a plan.
>> When I see my tribe mates at
the next immunity challenge,
I'll trick them into thinking
that I found the immunity idol.
>> PROBST: Misty returned to her
tribe at the immunity challenge
and helped the younger women
make a comeback.
Younger women have immunity.
Older men win immunity.
Younger men win immunity.
Older women going to Tribal
Council.
Before Tribal Council, Cirie
knew she was in trouble.
>> I'm really nervous.
I don't want to be the first
one to go home.
>> PROBST: So she campaigned to
have Tina voted out.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: But when Tina found a
fish, the decision was
complicated.
>> I do think that Cirie is the
weak link.
There are a hundred reasons to
keep Tina.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal Council
Tina ruffled feathers when she
criticized her tribe mates.
Do you think these other three
are pulling their weight?
>> Not as much as I would like.
>> No offense to Tina, but it's
not like she's out there
working and the three of us are
taking a nap.
>> PROBST: In the end, Cirie got
her wish when the older women
voted off their strongest
member.
Tina, the tribe has spoken.
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
(theme song playing)
(thunder)
>> Yo, it's such a drag because
shelter is somewhat useless
because the way the rain is
coming.
>> Yeah, how could we have
known?
>> Uh, well, the update is that
we're in a torrential downpour.
And our canopy wasn't completely
built, so we rushed to try and
get the palm fronds on there,
and we did it.
The problem is that the rain is
coming in from the other side
now, so a little bit of bad
luck.
This place breeds bad luck.
(thunder cracking)
>> Okay, we're getting close.
It's going out.
>> That's no good.
>> We don't have enough stuff
right here.
>> I feel like I want to hammer
the freaking thing!
(laughing)
>> Oh, shoot.
>> I got it.
>> That's it, honey.
Come on.
Oh, it's ripe.
Oh, we can eat this right now.
>> Almost.
>> It's going to be so good.
That's just me stabbing it.
>> You rock.
>> Nice job, girl.
>> Yeah!
>> Whoo!
>> I'm so happy.
>> Ta-dah...!
>> Mm, perfect.
>> Cheers.
>> Salud.
Papaya love.
>> Papaya love.
>> Sisters de bayoneta, our
first papaya.
>> Savor it.
>> I like it soft like that.
It's really juicy.
>> Okay, this is just...
I'm like, wow!
>> Mm...
>> It's almost orgasmically
wonderful, honestly.
>> Yeah!
>> It's so good.
Oh, it's like heaven.
I'm about to cry.
We have food.
>> It looks... it looks bad to
the west, and it looks bad to
the north.
>> You know, I think about
everything that I'm missing
right now.
I think about my kid.
I think about, you know, it's
football practice, and we have
a game Saturday, and I miss him
so much.
I miss my kid a lot.
I don't, you know, there's no...
there's no reason for me to be
doing this.
Like, we are going... I mean, I
more than enough money.
I don't know why I did this to
myself.
>> I don't like you, sand flea.
I don't like flea!
>> This whole scenario is so
different from the way that I
live my life.
Like, my life is very busy and
it's always all the time, it's
like constant, like ADD, you
know what I mean, psycho boy.
But I'm just... I have a real
hard time with the nothing-to-do
part.
I mean, there's plenty to do,
but it's monotonous, and it's
hard.
It's hard.
No more torrential downpours,
sir God!
No more of those!
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
You're getting your first look
at the new group of older women.
Tina voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
All right, let's get to it.
Everybody take a spot on the
disk.
Men on the light disks, women
on the dark disks.
Your choice.
Find one you like.
Okay, everybody take a step
back, flip over your disk.
If you see a buff, pick it up.
Terry, take a spot over here to
the left.
Danielle, over here to the
right.
Four tribes are about to become
two tribes.
Terry, you're the first member
of La Mina.
Danielle, you're the first
member of Casaya.
We're going to do a schoolyard
pick.
It doesn't matter who goes
first.
Because a man has to pick a
woman, a woman has to pick a
man.
Therefore, ladies first.
Danielle, you're choosing a man.
>> The cool guy with the Boston
tattoo.
>> The cool guy.
>> PROBST: Shane, here's the
buff, get rid of yours, put that
one on.
Terry, you're picking a woman.
>> Okay, uh... green sweats.
>> PROBST: Sally.
Here's the buffs.
Shane, picking a woman.
>> You're right there, little
lady.
>> PROBST: Courtney, now a
member of Casaya.
Sally, picking a guy.
>> I'll pick the fast guy, John
Deere hat.
>> PROBST: Austin becomes a
member of La Mina.
>> Nice to meet you all.
>> PROBST: Courtney.
>> Red shirt.
>> PROBST: Aras.
Deep sigh of relief to be on a
tribe.
Austin.
>> I'm going to go with Exile
Island over there.
>> PROBST: Misty becomes a
member of La Mina.
>> Misty.
Good to meet you.
>> Good to meet you.
>> PROBST: Aras, you're choosing
a woman.
>> Cirie.
Cirie?
>> PROBST: Cirie becomes a
member of Casaya.
>> Aras.
>> PROBST: Misty.
>> Nick.
>> PROBST: Nick becomes a member
of La Mina.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> PROBST: Cirie, your choice.
You're choosing a man.
>> This guy right here.
>> PROBST: Bobby joins Casaya.
Nick, your choice.
You're choosing a woman.
>> The young lady in the pink
tank top.
>> PROBST: Ruth Marie becomes a
member of La Mina.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> PROBST: Bobby, your choice
already been made for you.
>> Red shirt.
>> PROBST: Melinda joins Casaya.
(applause)
>> I'm Bobby.
>> Melinda.
>> PROBST: Okay, only one choice
left.
So, Ruth Marie, you are in
effect, choosing your last
tribe member, and also telling
one of these two guys nobody
wants him on their tribe.
>> This young man right here.
>> Thank you so much.
>> PROBST: Dan goes to La Mina.
>> I'm Nick.
>> Dan.
>> PROBST: Okay, so that leaves
you, Bruce.
>> My own tribe.
>> PROBST: How tough would it be
four days in to be going home?
>> I would be really
disappointed because I came
here to win.
>> PROBST: Well, not only are
you not going home, you, out of
all 15, are the only person
guaranteed to be safe at the
next Tribal Council.
>> Yeah, thank you!
Whoo!
>> PROBST: The next three days,
you're going to be spending on
Exile Island.
You won't return back to this
game until the next Tribal
Council.
At which point, you will sit in
and listen.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: After that tribe has
voted somebody out, you will
replace that person as the new
member of their tribe and be
back in this game.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: In addition, there's
still a hidden immunity idol
that may or may not be out
there.
Theoretically, Misty could
already have it.
>> I'm ready for this.
>> PROBST: Go.
The boat's out there.
You'll have flint waiting
for you, so you can make a fire.
>> Go, Bruce!
>> PROBST: Okay, two tribes-- La
Mina in orange; Casaya, wearing
purple.
Shall we get to today's reward
challenge?
(all agreeing)
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you are going to race
through an obstacle course,
collecting six wooden snakes
along the way.
One member of your tribe is
responsible for carrying all
six snakes throughout the
entire course.
On my "go," you'll make your
way to the first station, where
you will collect your first two
snakes.
Once you have those, you'll
crawl under a fence, over a
12-foot A-frame wall.
You'll make your way under the
bamboo crawl, grab two more
snakes.
You now have one person
carrying four snakes.
You then go across a ladder
bridge.
If you fall off the bridge, you
got to go back to the start
and go again.
For the last phase, you go
through the water and into a pit
of leaves, where you must find
the last two snakes.
First tribe to cross the finish
line with all six snakes wins
reward.
You want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Fishing gear.
>> Beautiful!
>> PROBST: In addition, waiting
for you at camp, one raft, four
paddles to go with it.
Should help you trying to
get some food.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: All right, let's take
our spots.
We'll get started.
La Mina, who is going to be
your snake wrangler?
Nick.
For Casaya, Courtney.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Both tribes pushing people up
quickly.
You've got to get the untied,
and one person is carrying them.
Danielle and Courtney have the
first snake untied for Casaya.
La Mina has their first snake.
Sally has the second snake for
La Mina.
Both tribes have both snakes.
Got to get everybody on the mat.
La Mina, go!
Casaya, go!
Both tribes are dead even.
When you have all seven over to
the other side, you can go.
>> Go, go, go!
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Carry those snakes.
That a way.
Casaya, go!
Two more snakes to collect on
your way through.
Both tribes pretty even.
Both snakes are free for La
Mina.
Both snakes are free for Casaya.
La Mina, go!
Casaya, go!
>> Take your time.
>> PROBST: Shane falls off,
heads back to the start.
This is going to be a challenge
for the snake wranglers.
It's a lot to handle.
Nick's across.
Move on!
Courtney's across.
Go!
Last stage.
We are neck and neck again.
Two snakes left buried in the
leaves.
>> Got one!
>> PROBST: Terry's got his hands
on one.
>> Got one, got one, got one.
>> PROBST: Aras has a snake
for Casaya.
>> I got it, I got it!
>> PROBST: Dan's released the
sixth one for La Mina.
They've got 'em all.
You got to get all six across
the finish.
La Mina wins reward!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Casaya, you guys
worked well together.
I don't even think you were
out-hustled.
You just loss.
I got nothing for you.
You're heading back to the
Casaya beach, previously the
older women's camp.
Head on out.
La Mina, nice effort, won
yourself a nice reward.
Come get it, head on out,
heading to the older men's camp.
>> It looks like a nice camp.
>> Yeah, this camp is so much
nicer than ours.
We didn't stop working.
I'm in a much better mood than
I was this morning.
I've always related better with
younger people.
I'm 34, but I'm definitely
young for my age in the way
that I think about life.
When I was at the older tribe,
I was thinking about every
single minute about when I was
gonna be leaving.
Here I haven't thought about,
you know what I mean, I
haven't thought about leaving
yet.
>> Do you all want to see your
new home?
>> We have not been wet at all.
>> I'm so impressed.
Why?
This is how we made ours.
>> Wow!
>> You see this, Bob?
>> We can add a little bit more
on this side to make it wider,
maybe.
>> How are the bugs?
>> Not bad.
>> You guys, this is definitely
the best spot for that.
>> You guys are awesome, man!
>> It's so great.
We're going to have fun.
>> This is so much better.
I'm so excited.
>> Oh, my God.
We have been invaded.
>> Fire!
Way to go, way to go, way to go.
I like our name.
I like our color.
I like our people.
First and foremost...
>> I mean, some of the people,
like Danielle, she's okay, and
Courtney, like, I mean, you
know, like, she, like...
>> I'm, like...
I'm, like, gangster Hollywood,
man.
I'm like near like Playboy,
liquor and stuff.
I'm, like, where the Hill
starts to rise, you know?
I can walk to Avalon.
>> It's like that game where
you have to figure out what
doesn't belong in a group, and
Cirie and I are the ones that
stick out.
>> it's so fun having so many
more people.
>> It's fun for me having girls
around.
I like having girls around.
>> If our tribe loses the
coming-up immunity challenge, I
think Cirie and I are screwed.
Yep, we're screwed.
>> I just have to get the
heat and now I'm happy.
>> What?
>> Yo, you, it's the three of
us.
It's the three of us and Aras.
>> Totally.
>> The four of us.
>> Here's the deal.
Can we not make it dramatic
and like cheat on each other
five people in, just the four of
us go to the four, done?
No more discussion about it.
If I just can get through this
part, which is the surviving,
and do well in the challenges,
we're going to be fine.
I got on the beach, and I was
right there.
I was like here it is, you,
you, you, you, let's lock
in right now.
You've just been welcomed into
the group.
I swear to you on my son's
life...
It's us four.
>> Yeah, totally, 100%.
>> For Shane, the first five
minutes we were there, he was
just like, "us four."
me, Shane, Aras and Courtney.
The people that don't talk and
communicate and see what's
going on and see how people
are feeling and look people in
the eye, they're the ones who
get voted off.
>> No way!
>> Oh, my God!
>> This is so awesome.
>> This is really nice.
>> Let's make sure we get some
poles, though.
I am thrilled with this outcome.
It was a close call for me.
I was the 15th guy picked, but
Ruth Marie did pick me, and this
was the team I definitely
wanted to be on.
>> Oh, fire!
It feels so good.
Thank you so much for letting
us come here.
>> Terry and I have a fantastic
relationship and a strategy
that's going to take us all the
way.
So it's great.
>> Dan and I were talking that
we'd like to make a bond with
you guys, look each other in the
eye, shake hands, and say, you
know, we're going to do our
best to get everyone to the
merge, but if we have to start
dropping people it's not going
to be one of us four guys.
>> It's in our best interest,
probably.
>> You have my word, you know,
you have my word, definitely.
>> What do you think?
>> It makes a lot of sense.
Terry just laid it out there.
He said him and Dan are together
and they want Austin and I with
them.
I think that him and Dan are
both strong players, both in the
challenges and around camp.
>> It's done.
>> Okay, thanks a lot, man.
>> Trust you, and I need you.
>> I trust you and I need you.
If we're gonna do this, I need
you.
>> We're gonna do this, all
right.
>> It makes sense for the short
term in the tribe.
The four of us really have
nothing to worry about with the
majority over the three women.
But, I don't know, you never
know what's going to happen.
>> So let's talk strategy for a
minute.
I talked to Misty a little bit,
and we were thinking if the
four of us stuck together,
meaning you and Nick, we would
have the numbers, and then it
feels kind of even because it's
you know, two girls, two guys,
and we can figure it out from
there, you know?
We would definitely want to vote
with you guys if you wanted to.
>> Okay.
>> So talk to Nick when you can.
>> All right, I will.
Cool.
It is definitely Austin and
Nick in the middle right now.
We are right in the middle of a
tug-of-war.
It lets me know that this game
is serious.
This isn't just all fun and
games.
Somebody is going to have to
get hurt out here.
>> "Clue one, day one.
You also have a lot of time
to think about why fate chose
you to be the first one out
here."
"Clue two, it is above the tide
line."
I read the clue.
The clue just showed me a
little section where the idol
is not.
Also it said it's above the
tide mark.
So I figured right against the
cliff someplace.
I'm going to be ripping this
island apart, and I'm going to
find that immunity idol.
That's where I'm going to put
most of my energy, after I get
the fire set up.
And it's a little bit miserable.
Inconvenience, that's all it is.
(murmuring)
It's all worn out.
(yells)
>> My practice will
really help me clear my mind,
focus, get my mind ready, like
for battle.
And then I get my mind ready
the same way to be on this
island.
>> This place is, like,
horrible, evil...
It's like not good to be here.
I would not wish this on my
worst enemy.
(thunderclap)
>> All right, I'm gonna go catch
us dinner.
>> Are you going to do the spear
and the goggles?
>> I never used one of those.
>> I haven't either.
We'll have to experiment with
that a little bit.
>> Yeah, let's play with it.
>> At the reward challenge, we
won fishing gear: spear gun,
hooks, tackle, a couple of drop
lines, fins and a mask and the
raft.
So it's pretty exciting.
It will be nice to get out
there and bring in some fish
for everybody.
Just point at the fish,
hopefully, and there you go.
>> That's kind of fun.
>> Just remember to hold on to
it.
>> I saw some fish just right
over there.
Look at them!
>> That's amazing.
Should we toss in a line?
>> Let's just see what it's
like down here.
>> Yeah, might as well.
We've paddled enough.
I was sitting on the edge of
the raft, and I decided I'm
going to try the spear, and I'm
like, oh, this will be a
practice shot.
So you...
Oh!
>> Uh-oh.
>> The first time I attempted to
use that stupid spear, it flew
off my arm, and I dove down,
and it was so deep.
>> Any sign of it?
>> I should have stuck to what
I knew.
>> That's all right.
Is it down 30, 40 feet,
probably?
>> I can't see anything.
>> Don't, like, stress out.
Don't, like, hurt yourself.
>> Nick was cool about it.
He was like just don't worry
about it, but I was really
nervous to come back and tell
the rest of the tribe.
I have some bad news.
>> What?
>> I lost that spear.
It was so... it was stupid.
>> Did it fall over or
something or fell through?
>> I'm so sorry.
>> Did you try to go back with
the mask?
>> It was so deep, I couldn't
get down there.
>> We were out about 100 yards,
probably 30, 40 feet of water.
>> I was very frustrated about
the spear.
I have no doubt in my mind we
would be eating tons of fish if
we had that spear.
>> I lost our spear.
I feel terrible.
>> Don't worry. We'll make...
We can make one.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Okay, how is everybody doing?
Misty, how're you hanging in
there?
>> Pretty good.
The good part about our team is
we're all very upbeat.
And that's kind of our rule:
Don't get down and out; just be
thankful and stay positive.
>> PROBST: Casaya, how are
things going for you?
>> I don't know how people
want to feel about stuff, but
I'm not gonna lie.
We are in a dire situation.
And you know, the whole like
"Ooh, let's act like we're
doing all right, so the other
tribe thinks we're..."
You know what I mean?
Screw that, we are not in a
good way.
Physically, we're wrecked.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
today's challenge.
Here's how it works: today's
immunity challenge will test
your ability to work together
while transporting a giant
zombie head from the ocean to
the beach.
Each tribe has a boat.
That boat is anchored to the
bottom of the ocean floor with a
large wooden box.
In addition, each boat has six
holes, filled with rubber plugs.
On my "Go," five tribe members
pull out the plugs and begin
bailing the water that is now
coming in the boat.
The other two tribe members
jump into the water, start
moving the boat forward by
pulling the anchor, which is
very heavy.
Once you get to shore, clip
your boat into the hitching
post.
You must now transport the
anchor up the beach to your
finish mat.
The first tribe to get their
zombie head on the zombie body
wins immunity, safe from Tribal
Council.
Losers, somebody going home
tonight; big enough stakes?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Swim out, we'll get
started.
For immunity...
Survivors ready?
Go!
Aras in the water for Casaya.
Bobby's right behind.
Going to have to work together
to keep that water out of the
boat!
Terry and Nick in the water for
La Mina.
Casaya's going backwards.
Nick and Austin going to switch
it up for La Mina.
>> PROBST: Bobby and Shane
swapping out for Casaya.
Shane made zero progress in the
water.
La Mina still in the lead but
only because Casaya is
absolutely inept.
Casaya switching out members
again.
>> You take the back.
I'll take the front.
>> PROBST: Casaya making up some
ground.
>> Go, let's go!
>> PROBST: Casaya getting
closer.
La Mina, got to pick it up!
Terry pulling that anchor in.
La Mina's first back to the
beach.
Casaya not giving up.
Get that anchor to the shore.
Get that boat clipped in.
>> Pull!
>> PROBST: The boat is stuck.
La Mina trying to muscle it in.
Still a few inches short.
Casaya starting to close the
gap.
Misty's got it clipped!
The boat is done.
Get the anchor to the finish
mat.
>> Pull.
>> Come on, come on!
>> Come on, hurry!
(indistinct shouts)
>> PROBST: Casaya still has a
shot.
La Mina very close.
(indistinct shouts)
You're good.
Get the head on the body for
immunity.
>> Get closer.
>> You got it.
>> PROBST: La Mina wins
immunity!
(cheering)
(muttering)
La Mina, immunity.
>> Whoo-whoo!
>> PROBST: No Tribal Council.
Congratulations.
Casaya, Tribal Council tonight.
It's going to cost you a member.
You have the afternoon to
figure out who that's going to
be.
See you at Tribal tonight.
>> Whenever there's a
competition of any sort, I don't
like to lose, you know, I just,
uh, I hate to lose anything.
I'm beat. I'm wiped-out.
I want a cigarette.
I want a coffee.
I want to have a big sandwich.
I want to call my kid.
I want to tell him I love him
and this is just the stupidest
thing I ever did in my whole
life.
I am not well without him.
I'm not well without him.
>> Shane, what are you doing?
>> It's not what I'm doing or
what I'm not doing.
I'm telling you, I can't finish.
I'm gonna quit. I have to quit.
>> Come on.
>> It only gets better from
here, we're gonna win food...
>> Really, just give it a
chance, please.
Don't fall down on this moment.
>> What's up?
>> He's just not feeling so
good right now.
>> Emotionally? Physically?
>> I just, you know, I don't
want to be here anymore.
Like, I really just want you
guys to vote me off.
>> That's nuts.
>> We need you, man.
I mean, you're dropping on us,
too, you know that, right?
>> I'm not dropping on you guys.
>> Yeah, you are.
Shane is letting us down
completely.
He's leaving us high and dry,
and I just feel like he snapped
today and threw in the towel.
I mean, it's just like, come
on, man, pick it up!
>> Where is he?
>> Just when we thought it was
over, Shane wants to quit.
Aahh!
You have people begging to stay
here.
If somebody wants to quit, let
him quit.
>> So you, basically this is
what'll happen.
You're gonna, you know, we're
gonna be here.
We're going to have water.
And we're going to have food
tomorrow, you'll be set.
And we'll be eating not like a
champion...
>> I don't want to be here.
>> Are you sure?
>> I'm positive. I'm positive.
I'm sorry.
>> Shane, come back here.
You-You know that thought was
in your head.
>> I just don't want to, like,
if I get hydrated, and I get
food...
>> Just try it. Okay?
>> Okay. All right.
>> Just 'cause it's not like I
can do anything.
>> I know, but...
>> We can just bring it up
right now.
Hey, guys, I hate to be the one
to bring this up...
>> Oh, no.
>> But Shane wants to stay.
He doesn't want to go home.
>> I'm really sorry about my,
like, insanity flip-flop today.
It's like there's no reason why
I shouldn't try and stay.
I haven't had water in two days.
It's like, if I drink, I might
feel better in my brain and in
my head, and I might want to
stay, you know what I mean?
So like...
>> And so now we have to talk
about who we're going to vote
off.
So, I'm... I just want to do
this with honesty and like
openness, and-and where I stand
here is, like, I want our tribe
to be as physically strong as
possible.
So, I think, like, for me, I
per... and this is nothing
against you two, either one, but
I'm going to throw my vote
either with you or you.
And I haven't decided yet.
Cirie, you're looking at me
like you hate me, and I...
>> No, I just don't...
What do you want me...
I don't know what to say about
that.
>> Well, since you just dropped
this bomb on here, seriously...
>> I just wanted... I just
wanted to put it out there.
>> Jason just dropped a huge
bomb, like, boom!
>> I don't want anyone to show
up at Tribal Council and have
their back stabbed.
>> Aras literally came over to
the shelter, not having spoken
to anyone about what he was
about to do, and he said, "Cirie
or Melinda are going to go home
tonight."
It was so stupid.
And it was his decision.
He just came over and was like,
"Boop!"
>> There's been an arrangement
obviously made.
What he said sounded insincere.
I don't know what to tell you.
Like, I don't care which one of
you goes.
You know what I mean?
I just don't...
Like, whoever doesn't go now
is going next.
>> And then Shane piped in, you
know, that yeah, it's the four
of us, like literally just said
right out loud that we have an
alliance.
You don't let...
You don't tell everyone what's
going on.
If this total instability
continues, it's going to be
very hard to know that he will
be there for us.
>> We're screwed.
I think it's me.
I think it's me, and whatever.
There's nothing I can do right
now.
I'm going to stop... (mumbles.)
>> I don't know who's going to
go first.
Cirie seems to think she'll go
first, but I-I'm not so sure
that it won't be me.
>> I... I feel so awful.
I don't like this.
>> (crying): Yeah, there's a lot
about it that's not fair.
There really is.
I was the last one picked of
our group, so that's one reason
that I think it might be me.
And I'm not all, "Ooh,
meditative, cool, yeah."
That's just not me.
>> I mean, it's one or the
other at this point.
Cirie and Melinda are going to
go one-two, whatever, you know.
They're the first two to go.
The thing I don't feel safe
about is my brain giving up.
Like, I have this part of me
that wants to go into Tribal
Council tonight and just say,
"Listen, cut me out, because
I don't, I don't want to be here
anymore."
>> PROBST: For those of you who
don't have torches, there's one
behind you.
Go ahead and grab it and
approach the flame, dip it in
and get fire.
This is part of the ritual at
Tribal Council, because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire,
you're in the game.
When the fire is gone, so are
you.
We'll now bring in Bruce from
Exile Island.
During Tribal Council, Bruce is
just listening in, trying to
get a gauge of the tribe
dynamics.
Once the vote's over, he will
join this tribe, go back to
camp with you guys.
Shane, you made no bones about
it at the challenge today.
You said, "Jeff, I'm not going
to pretend for the other tribe
that everything's fine.
It's miserable."
>> Yeah, it's the worst thing
that has ever happened to me in
my entire life.
Like I wanted to quit.
I wanted them all to write my
name down and I wanted to leave
here because I couldn't get out
of the mania of dehydration,
not being able to eat, and on
top of that, I smoke three
packs of cigarettes a day, and
quit the day I got here, so
I'm in the midst of this insane
withdrawal from that, and I was
done.
I wanted out of here.
>> PROBST: So is this like a
detox for you?
>> It's like, it's some kind of
psychotic, bad-idea detox.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Cirie, let's talk
about what's going on at camp
life.
>> I think for the most part,
everybody was okay with
everyone else, up until today.
>> PROBST: What happened today?
>> Well, no matter how happy
you try to be, it's hard to
stay like that when you're
told, "It's us four," and
that's basically what it was.
And either one of y'all are
going to go home today.
It's hurtful.
I mean, I'm human.
>> Especially when I think in
the challenges that we have
competed together in the team.
I don't think that there's
anything that Cirie or I did or
didn't do that they have
point... that they could point
out to and say, "You should
have done that better."
>> PROBST: So if it's you
tonight, just the way it goes?
>> No.
I mean, I'm disappointed.
I'm pissed.
I'm... hurt.
It bothers me when somebody
even remotely had the thought
to quit, and you have me here
who is trying my best to stay.
>> PROBST: Cirie, if it's you
tonight, six days is not bad.
>> Six days isn't bad, but the
disappointment that my family
would have is bad.
>> PROBST: Why would they be
disappointed in you?
You're giving it your all.
>> My family might not be
disappointed, but I will be
disappointed for them,
because part of the reason I
come... came here was to help
them, so...
They probably wouldn't be, um,
disappointed... but I would.
>> PROBST: To me, this tribe
seems a little all over the map.
I'm curious to see how it plays
out.
It is time to vote.
Cirie, you're up.
>> (whispering): Shane, you made
me promise that I would vote for
you, and I don't go back on a
promise.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Shane.
Two votes Shane.
Melinda.
One vote Melinda.
That's two votes Shane, two
votes Melinda.
Three votes Melinda, two votes
Shane.
Second person voted out of
Survivor Exile Island: Melinda.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Melinda, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Take care.
>> PROBST: Bruce, drop your
buff.
Join your new tribe, Casaya.
>> How are you doing?
Yeah, brother.
Hey, brother.
>> PROBST: Here's your buff.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I came out here to play the
game.
>> PROBST: The La Mina women
have a plan.
>> is it working?
>> I think it is.
>> PROBST: things get dirty at
the challenge...
(grunting and groaning)
...and sparks fly at Casaya.
>> You're out of your mind,
man.
You are crazy!
>> I want one!
This one!
I just want mine!
>> I just found myself on the
tribe that's like, "Hey, man,
yo, dude, what's up?"
And that's just not me.
It won't ever be me, nor do I
think I want it to be me, so I
just wish Cirie luck because I
know she didn't want to go back
there without me.
It's just going to be hell.
But I'm going to have a shower,
and I'm going to drink water,
and I'm going to eat food!