>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> I have to make fire from
scratch.
>> Here another day, my man.
>> PROBST: Terry, Sally and
Austin face discouraging odds
against the six remaining former
Casaya tribe mates.
>> They're sitting there all
happy because they have the
numbers.
But if I can draw two of
those people over to our side,
the tables could turn.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the Survivors were
randomly divided into three
teams and played for breakfast
in bed.
Bruce, Aras, Sally win reward!
Who's going to Exile Island?
>> Austin.
>> PROBST: This time the winners
were forced to send two people
to Exile Island.
Austin, Danielle, the boat's
waiting for you.
While Sally, Bruce and Aras
enjoyed breakfast in bed,
Danielle and Austin suffered
together on Exile Island.
>> Out of all the people that I
had to get stuck on the island,
I'm glad it was Austin.
I have a little bit more trust
built with him.
Logically, Austin would be,
you know, a backup plan.
>> PROBST: Back at camp, Terry
tricked Shane into revealing the
Casaya pecking order.
>> I found out some very
important stuff.
Danielle and Bruce are next on
the pecking order.
And if I can get those guys over
to our side, this will totally
swing the game.
>> PROBST: Go!
At the immunity challenge, Terry
won individual immunity for the
second time in a row.
Terry wins immunity!
Back at camp, Terry and Austin
immediately cornered Bruce to
try to get him to flip.
>> They're concocting their
plan.
You're not part of it, Bruce.
Your only chance is with us.
>> If I'm at the bottom of the
Casaya pecking order, then
everything's up for grabs.
>> Hold on. Let me get in the
middle.
>> PROBST: Then Austin and Terry
made a bold promise to Danielle.
>> It's tempting that I could
actually transform this game
into a whole new thing.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Danielle and Bruce stay
true to their alliance.
Terry kept his hidden immunity
idol.
The eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island, the
first member of our jury.
And Austin was voted out.
Austin, the tribe has spoken.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> And you're at four years at
which university?
>> First, flight school for Navy
is Pensacola.
Then I went to jet training in
Meridian, Mississippi where you
learn to dogfight and drop
bombs and shoot guns and land on
the carrier.
And then you get your wings from
there.
And then from there you go to,
you know, say, Jacksonville for
A-7s or F-18s, Whidbey Island
for...
>> He's a retired Naval pilot?
>> And I'm already behind the
curve and he slaps nine Gs on
our way. (grunts) Wham!
And my head just goes up
against the canopy...
>> How is any normal American
person supposed to beat a Navy
air fighter pilot dude?
>> Maybe he'll break his arm or
something.
>> (chuckles): God forbid.
>> Oh, my God, I can't believe
you just said that.
>> I know. I'm sorry.
>> All right, guys, here's the
question.
>> That's not in our plan.
>> That's not part of the plan,
Terry.
>> All right, then I'm just
gonna have to take you to the
bank the whole time.
>> If you do that, man, hats
off.
>> Tribal Council last night was
kind of a bummer.
Austin went home; that was the
end result, but prior to that,
there was a big swing play to
try to get Danielle to come
over by offering her the hidden
immunity idol, and, uh, she
declined.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> So now Sally and I are pretty
much on our own, so my mindset
is, I am totally motivated to
kick their butts at everything
that comes down the road.
>> Where's his bag?
>> I want to see it.
Is it something fuzzy?
>> Before Austin went home,
Terry showed me some sort of
hidden immunity idol.
I mean, it was something furry.
I mean, he could be making this
up and he could have just, I
don't know, found, I guess, this
furry thing out in the woods and
could be showing it to me
pretending like it's the hidden
idol, but I don't know.
You have to be careful who you
assume has it.
>> I just had a nice long talk
with Terry about his time in the
Navy.
>> I mean, it's, like, it's
pretty cool that we're going up
against that guy.
>> (sarcastic): Yeah, really
cool.
>> We're gonna take him out.
>> All right.
>> He flies planes.
He's not...
>> Yeah, but he went to the
Naval Academy, dude.
>> He's not an American
Gladiator, you know?
>> This reward challenge, if any
of you guys win it and don't
take me, send my ass to Exile
Island.
>> Sure you want to go?
>> I don't know if someone's
found the hidden immunity idol,
and I want to go figure that out
for myself because I'm
absolutely a target going into
these next Tribal Councils, and
I want to be there on that
island scouring it and see
what I can find.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
How's everybody doing?
>> Great.
>> Marvelous.
>> PROBST: Today I'm gonna tell
you what you're playing for
before I tell you about the
challenge.
It's been 22 days since you have
seen or heard from anyone back
home.
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: And that's long
enough.
So to whet your appetite for
today's challenge, I'm gonna
give you just a little taste of
love from home.
Follow me.
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: Have a seat.
Well, it would be great if they
were here in the flesh.
They're not, but they did send
some videos from home that will
hopefully fill your heart a
little bit.
This is just a taste of what's
on your video.
Win today's reward challenge,
and you get to watch the whole
thing.
Terry, this is your wife Trish,
your son Danny...
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: ...your daughter
Kayla and your dog Riley.
>> Riley.
>> You've been gone for a long
time now.
It seems like forever.
>> Daddy, I really miss you, and
I want you to come home.
I hope you're doing good.
Outwit, outplay, outlast.
I really miss you.
(clapping)
>> That was awesome.
>> PROBST: Danielle, here's your
whole family.
>> Oh, geez.
>> Hi, Danielle.
I miss you, and I can't wait to
see you.
It's not the same around here
without you here bothering me.
>> We love you very much and
very, very proud of everything
you're doing.
>> PROBST: Bruce, here's your
family.
You've got your wife Nancy, your
daughter Danielle, and I think
there's a dog.
>> Chaco.
>> PROBST: Chaco.
>> Chaco, where's Bruce?
>> Where's Dad?
(barks)
>> Oh. Oh, oh.
Ah.
She misses you.
Yeah, she's a good watchdog, but
she's not like having the real
guy here.
>> PROBST: How long you been
married?
>> Almost 28 years.
>> PROBST: 28 years.
>> Yeah. I'm more in love with
her than when I first met her.
>> PROBST: How do you think
she's doing back home without
you around?
>> I'm sure she misses my
snoring, so she can't sleep
well.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Courtney, here's
your mom Barbara.
>> Sweetheart, you just have to
know that we are thinking about
you every single day.
We've got the candles going,
we've got the fountain going,
we've got the love signs going,
and we've got the prayers going.
We love you very much.
Bye, hon.
>> This is our love sign, like,
in our family.
That's my mom's, and this is my
dad, and this is my sister's.
And, like, so our whole family
has these love signs, and it's
really great.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: Aras, this is your
dad.
>> Hey, Aras.
(laughter)
Long time no see.
Remember when you used to do
this?
Anyways, come in with tepee.
I have something I want to tell
ya.
>> PROBST: The tepee in your
backyard?
What's that about?
>> My dad's always wanted a
tepee, and five years ago, his
sister bought one for him, so we
just have fires out there, and
we'll sit and talk.
>> PROBST: Sounds like you have
a strong connection with your
dad.
>> I do, so it's really nice to
see.
>> PROBST: All right, Shane,
safe to say the love of your
life, your son Boston?
>> (voice breaking): Not even a
question.
>> Hey, Dad, it's me.
I love you so much, and I know
that you're doing fine out
there.
Say hi to Loki.
(Shane sobbing)
>> PROBST: What are you feeling
now?
Are you wishing you were home?
Are you feeling good 'cause you
saw him?
>> We grew up together.
You know, I was 21 when I had
him.
He is my other half, he is my
brother, he is my best friend,
he is my son, he is my life.
>> PROBST: All right, Sally,
here's your mom, dad, you sister
and even your dog Darby.
>> Hi, Sal.
We're all sitting here in my new
place that I can't wait for you
to see.
We're all rooting for you, and
we all miss you very much.
We love you!
>> Love you, Sal.
I love you, Sal.
>> PROBST: So your sister got a
new apartment since you've been
gone?
>> Apparently.
>> PROBST: All right, so
everybody's had a taste...
Aw.
(laughter)
I couldn't forget you, Cirie.
Here's your son Jared and
Jamil and your husband H.B.
>> Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
>> Hey, Mom.
>> Hey, honey bunny.
We missed you a lot, honey.
>> Yes...
>> Yes. It ain't the same
without you being around here.
We miss your laugh, your smile,
just everything.
>> PROBST: Does that make you
wish you were home, or are you
just feeling better now that
you've seen them?
>> I'm happy that I saw... saw
them, but it makes it harder for
me here.
(Cirie sniffles and sighs)
But all of this is for them,
so...
>> PROBST: Win today's reward
challenge, you get to see the
rest of your video, and you'll
enjoy something else that will
make you think of home-- peanut
butter and jelly sandwiches...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: ...and ice cold milk.
>> Ah!
>> PROBST: Want to hear about
the challenge?
>> Yes!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, you're
going to divide into two teams
of four, and you will most
definitely have to work together
to win this.
One person will lie face-down
on a cradle that is suspended in
the air by bungee cords.
Attached to that cradle are
three ropes.
The other three people on your
team will pull those ropes to
maneuver the person on the
cradle as they grab 15 flags and
place them in order, one at a
time, in their appropriate
slots.
First tribe to get all 15 in
order wins reward.
In addition, the winning team of
four decides who goes to Exile
Island.
All right, we're going to
randomly divide into two even
teams of men and women.
Let's go.
Okay, in the white cradle, we
have Courtney being pulled by
Bruce, Sally, Terry.
In the black cradle, it's
Danielle being pulled by Aras,
Cirie and Shane.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Got to get the flags one at a
time and in order.
>> Get it! Get it!
>> PROBST: Danielle has the
first flag.
>> Good. This way, this way.
>> PROBST: She's got it in the
slot.
Looking for flag number two.
Courtney has her first flag.
>> Get down and pull.
Come on, let's go.
>> PROBST: And it's in.
>> Where to?
>> This way, this way.
>> Come on, other side.
Go inside, inside, inside!
>> PROBST: Bruce, Sally, Terry
trying to get Courtney turned
around.
>> Turn around, Court.
>> PROBST: Danielle has her
second flag.
Cirie, Aras, Shane pull it
right into the slot.
>> Three's over there.
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
Take her over, take her over!
>> Come on.
>> We got to work all together.
>> Okay.
>> Three's on the other side.
Other side. Let's go...
>> Hey, back over here.
>> I got it, I got it.
>> Okay, let's go this way.
>> PROBST: Danielle on to her
third flag.
Cirie, Shane, Aras working very
well.
>> This way, this way.
>> Get her over there.
All three, all three, all three.
Run, run, run, run, run!
>> PROBST: Courtney has her
third flag.
>> Where's four?
>> To your left.
Up high, up high.
Come on, swing me, swing me!
Swing me!
>> All right, now.
>> PROBST: Danielle gets it, has
the fourth flag!
>> Get up, up!
>> Hold on.
>> Over there.
Okay, okay.
>> I got the flag.
>> You got it.
>> PROBST: Danielle has her
fifth flag, and it's in.
Don't knock those flags out.
>> Come on, Shane!
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Courtney, Bruce,
Sally, Terry trying to stay in
this.
>> Fourth tie, fourth tie!
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Danielle with flag
number six.
Courtney right behind with her
sixth flag.
>> You got?
>> PROBST: We are tied, six-six.
Both teams with their seventh
flag.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Flying back to put it
in the slot.
Shane, Aras, Cirie get Danielle
there.
We're tied, seven-seven.
>> On this side, right behind
you.
>> Okay.
>> Pull, Shane.
>> Come on, Shane, come on!
>> PROBST: Danielle has flag
number eight.
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Courtney has her
eighth flag.
>> Come on. It's over here.
>> Get down.
Get down and pull.
Come on, pull, pull, pull!
>> Here, here, here!
>> Watch.
>> Aah!
>> PROBST: Oh, got to go back.
Aras knocked a flag out.
Got to get that first flag back
in the slot, and that's going to
cost them some time.
>> Now!
>> Oh, yeah, got it...
>> PROBST: Terry, Sally, Bruce
have a good system now!
>> Come on, come on!
Come on!
>> Watch your feet.
>> Let's go!
>> Where's ten?
>> Ten right here.
(Danielle grunts and sighs)
>> PROBST: Danielle frustrated.
Can't get it in.
>> Aah!
>> PROBST: She has it.
Don't knock it out.
>> Careful!
Careful, Shane!
>> PROBST: Courtney with the
eleventh flag.
Shane, Aras, Cirie going to have
to make up some time right now.
>> Come on, guys!
(grunts)
>> Where's Shane?
>> Shane right through there.
>> Whoa.
>> Be careful, be careful.
(grunting)
>> PROBST: Courtney, Terry,
Bruce, Sally now lead 12-nine.
Danielle, another flag has been
knocked down.
>> Keep it tight!
(laughs)
I can't get it!
>> Courtney, it's right here.
>> Pull me down more!
>> PROBST: Terry, Sally, Bruce,
Courtney have one flag left.
(Bruce grunting)
>> Come on!
>> Take the... Take your time!
Take your time!
>> Swing me, swing me!
(grunting)
>> PROBST: Loved one's video,
peanut butter and jelly
sandwiches, ice cold milk.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Reward for Courtney,
Terry, Bruce and Sally!
>> Yes!
Again, the factor!
>> Damn.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Okay, before we get
to the rest of the your reward,
big decision.
You're sending one person to
Exile Island.
Is it going to be Danielle,
Aras, Cirie or Shane?
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Who's it going to be?
>> Aras.
>> PROBST: Aras, get your stuff.
The boat's coming to pick you
up.
>> Bye, Aras.
>> PROBST: Shane, Cirie,
Danielle, I'm genuinely sorry
that the rest of the afternoon
doesn't include you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Enjoy your families, guys.
>> See you.
>> Thoughts with you guys.
>> PROBST: Okay, now comes the
fun-- videos and peanut butter
and jelly.
Let's go.
(indistinct chatter)
(laughter)
>> You know what I mean?
So, let's just...
If you're going to lose one,
let's lose this one.
The tapes would have wrecked
us, dude.
>> I know.
>> Shane and Danielle and
myself returned to camp.
Shane kind of said this wasn't
like the hugest challenge to
lose, but he was just trying to,
uh, kind of lift our spirits.
Yay! Home!
>> I have an issue with my
penis.
(Cirie laughs)
I'm so sorry.
>> Then, Shane had a medical
emergency.
(Cirie laughs)
>> Oh, something's really going
on.
I need you to look at it real
quick.
>> (laughing): I don't want to
look at it.
>> You're a nurse!
>> I know.
>> Can you explain it to me, or
do I have to look at it?
>> Shane has this funky thing
going on with his, uh,
testicles, to put it nicely.
Lucky me, being the only nurse
out here, he wanted me to take a
look at 'em.
(Cirie laughs)
Yay!
>> Don't be laughing.
>> All right.
>> Hey, don't laugh.
It's a... not a...
Here.
(Cirie laughs)
>> What?!
>> That's because it's wet all
the time.
Your clothes are moist.
It's like chafing.
You know, like diaper rash on a
baby?
>> Yeah. That's what that is?
>> I tried to be as professional
as I could under the
circumstances, but it was just
so hilarious.
(Cirie laughing)
>> Is that because I've been
wearing those undies for 23
days?
>> It's a good guess, Shane.
>> How do I make that go away?
>> Can you dry it out?
>> What's wrong with him?
>> Just like a little red, and
then he's naked.
Oh, my God.
>> Yo.
I'm eating.
(Cirie sighs)
>> Can I do a skirt glove?
>> No. Do your shirt.
Do your shirt.
>> I guess.
>> Shane is like a cartoon
character, and now he's like a
nude cartoon character, but that
helped me so much, because I
kind of forgot about what I was
missing.
>> Ladies, it's my chafing
skirt.
>> Okay.
(bird singing)
>> There's two reasons I'm
really happy to be out here.
One, I get to spend some time by
myself and really step away from
the game.
And, two, I get a chance to look
for the immunity idol.
Immunity is very important, and
the hidden immunity idol is,
obviously, clearly, very
important, but I just can't seem
to wrap my mind around these
clues.
One of the problems with the
clue is that it says it's under
a rock.
People have moved rocks, so, I
don't know if I'm digging a hole
where there is nothing to dig,
or I don't know what's going on.
I'm sure a lot of that just has
to do with mental fatigue of
being out here for days.
>> Terry is the person I fear
may have the idol.
It would be a real easy move on
his part to just send me out
here, knowing I'm his biggest
physical competitor, and that,
you know, it might weaken me
physically to be out here.
So his quickness to send me
might suggest that there is no
immunity idol out here, so
there's no sense in me looking
for it.
>> Yo, they're home.
>> Are we...?
>> Boo, boo, boo.
When Sally and the other team
that won-- when they came back,
I didn't even want to see them.
I was just kind of like already
aggravated that we lost, and the
last thing I want to know is how
full their bellies are, and how
great it was to see their
families.
>> Oh, you guys got your luxury
items, too?
>> Yeah.
>> Hey.
>> You always want to learn how
to swing a shovel.
>> You guys get to learn our
fire dance.
>> And then, you know, when they
walked back in, and they all had
their luxury items, I'm, like,
oh, wow, you know, that's a
double whammy.
>> It's all right, honey.
You can't...
You guys won.
You know what I mean?
>> I know.
>> You need help, Terry?
>> After the food for the soul
and the heart with the videos
came luxury items for us four
members.
It was great.
Just kind of hook this in for
now.
(Bruce mumbles)
Thank you for asking me.
Both my father-in-law and my
father were Korean war vets,
and, uh... and they recently
passed away, and this was on my
father-in-law's casket.
So in order to honor both my
father and my father-in-law,
going to hang here at, uh,
Gitanos for a while, and, uh,
hopefully till day 39.
>> What did you guys, what did
you bring?
Love it!
>> Sally brought her journal,
Bruce has a sketchbook, and
Terry has the American flag, go
figure.
But I thought Courtney's luxury
items were like the coolest.
(Courtney laughing)
>> It makes me so happy, you
know.
It's a toy for everyone.
It's really fun.
This is, like, my-my joy.
>> But it's hard when you're
the loser, and everybody is
like (laughing): "I got this!
And look what I...!"
Who cares?
You know, you want to say, "Who
cares?
Get out of here," but you can't.
It's a game, so you have to
kind of keep it together.
(birds screeching)
>> Then it's up to you to
either get Courtney, Danielle,
or Cirie to come over and one
of us would have to win the
next challenge.
That way we could share the
hidden immunity idol, and we
would have numbers.
>> There are currently six
ex-Casaya members that are
staying loyal and true to each
other, versus Terry and I, the
two ex-La Mina members who are
left.
Like, what if we said to, like,
Danielle or Courtney or whoever,
say, like, you or I won the next
immunity, and we said, we're
going to play that thing
tonight, so you better jump on
now.
>> You know, we could play the
hidden immunity idol, and we
could, you know, one of us will
be immune.
So one of you are going home.
>> If Terry or I win immunity
today, and Terry decides that
he wants to play the hidden
immunity idol, one of the other
six ex-Casaya members will go
home tonight.
Because the immunity idol can
be used after the vote is made,
which means we would all have to
show our cards and then the next
person who has the most votes
would get kicked off, and so I
have a lot of hope that things
could change today in this game.
>> What do we have to do other
than beat you at immunity?
Do you know of anything?
>> I don't know, you better not
think about anything else.
>> How about this: if you don't
win immunity, and you don't
have that silly idol from that
goofy island, you're gone.
>> Yeah, well, you never know.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Hello.
>> Good morning.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
Aras, returning from Exile
Island.
>> Morning, beast.
>> Hey.
>> What's up, fellas?
(applause)
>> A day and a half of
meditation never hurt nobody.
>> Brucey.
>> PROBST: Aras, two days out
there.
How was it?
>> It was surprisingly nice.
I made fire, like, the first
three minutes.
I ate a lot, I hydrated myself
really well.
I got a little time for myself
and a little time to look for
the idol.
>> PROBST: So overall, Exile
Island was not that bad?
>> No, but I don't know if I'd
want to go right back.
>> PROBST: All right, before we
get to the challenge, I'm going
to hand each of you a nut and a
shell.
Without conferring with anybody,
put the shell in one hand, put
the nut in the other hand.
I'll explain how these come
into play in a minute.
And I'll take the immunity
necklace from you.
Immunity, once again back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, this is
how it works: sitting on the
ocean floor is a long plank
with seven symbols on it.
On my "go," you're going to
swim out, memorize as many of
those symbols, in order, as you
can, then race back to the
beach where you will attempt to
replicate those symbols in the
same order on your answer board.
The first person to solves it
correctly, wins immunity,
guaranteed a one in seven shot
at $1 million.
Losers, Tribal Council tonight,
and for one of you, this game
will come to an end.
Now, there's a twist to today's
challenge: if immunity is just
not that important to you, you
don't have to take part in
today's challenge.
Instead, you can chow down...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: ...on cheeseburgers,
French fries...
>> Me.
>> PROBST: ...and soft drinks.
You can eat for as long as the
challenge goes, or until the
food runs out.
Put the shell in one hand, put
the nut in the other hand.
When I tell you to reveal if
you want to take part in the
challenge, you will show me the
shell.
If instead you want to eat
food, you'll show me the nut.
Three, two, one, reveal.
Okay, Aras is going to take
part in the challenge.
Sally is taking part in the
challenge.
Terry is taking part in the
Bruce, Cirie, Courtney, Shane,
and Danielle are all saying, "I
don't need immunity.
I'm going to eat."
You five take a spot on the
picnic table.
The other three, down here at
the answer booth.
>> Aras, it's all you.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, it's Terry
Aras, and Sally fighting for
immunity while Shane, Danielle,
Courtney, Cirie, and Bruce chow
down and enjoy the show.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Got to swim out, memorize the
symbols in order.
Shane digging in, Danielle
digging in.
Cirie already got a bite.
Bruce not waste any time.
We have two challenges going on.
How much food can you get down
before somebody wins immunity?
Terry going down.
Aras taking a dip to look.
Sally taking a dip to look.
A lot of French fries, a lot of
cheeseburgers.
Terry thinks he has it
memorized.
He's coming back.
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: Aras heading back.
Sally still working on it.
Five very secure people chowing
down.
Terry first back.
He's going to give a go.
Aras right behind him.
Sally heading back.
You're looking to get all seven
symbols in the same order.
>> Go, Sally!
>> PROBST: Sally making her way
back.
Sally trying to work hers out
up top before she commits.
>> Take your time, guys.
>> PROBST: Who's on their second
burger?
Shane and Cirie.
Bruce on his second burger.
Terry working it out.
Immunity on the line.
No.
Aras doesn't have it.
Aras swimming back out for
another look.
>> Here you go.
>> PROBST: Terry thinks he has
it.
>> Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh.
>> PROBST: Terry wins immunity
for the third straight time!
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yes...!
Yes!
>> PROBST: Stop eating.
Put it down.
Put it down, guys.
Terry, come on over.
For the third straight time,
individual immunity.
You're safe at Tribal Council.
With this around your neck, you
cannot be voted out.
For the other seven of you,
after 24 days, tonight, this
game will come to an end for one
of you.
Head on back to camp.
See you at Tribal.
(laughing quietly)
>> Did you get the clue?
>> Yeah, I got the clue.
But it's hard to find.
>> Oh, really?
>> No, no, there are two
choices.
Either it was really easy to
find and he got it right away.
>> Oh, right.
>> Or... or no one's got it.
>> So, we vote Sally, 6-0
tonight...
>> Okay.
>> ...and hope to God he
doesn't have it?
>> Yeah.
Thanks for standing up for
Casaya.
>> I should have won it.
Today's immunity challenge,
anybody who wanted to not
participate in the challenge
could sit and have
cheeseburgers.
There was no question what I
was going to do, because it's
very possible that I could go
home today.
If Sally ends up having the
hidden immunity idol, then
Sally and Terry's vote will
knock somebody out.
>> I think Terry just showed
the hidden immunity idol.
Until this moment, I really was
kind of questionable about him
having the immunity idol, but I
believe that is the immunity
idol, and I'm looking forward
to seeing what happens tonight.
>> Tonight... if two of you
said we will vote with you...
>> Aras.
>> If two of us would vote with
you guys...
>> The goal was to get two
people, so it would be Terry,
myself, and two others.
It'd be four against four, we'd
have the idol, we'd play it, and
what he wants to see happen is
us break up 'cause it's going to
happen anyway, so he's like,
"Why don't a couple of you want
to guarantee yourself a spot in
the final four?"
I'm giving everybody in camp the
impression that the hidden
immunity idol will be played
tonight.
Terry may decide that it isn't
worth giving up the idol at this
point, but it's most
advantageous for us to break up
this strong six as soon as
possible and watch them unravel
and watch them scurry a bit.
Otherwise, I'm gone.
>> You're saying that you're
giving your immunity idol to
Sally?
>> I'm not saying I have it.
I'm just saying it's out there
and it could be put in play
tonight, and what I am proposing
is getting Bruce on our side and
then get somebody else like you
to come over and make it a
guaranteed four and then we'll
vote the four votes for Aras and
then he'll be gone.
>> I can't-- I can't commit to
this at this moment.
>> Okay.
Guaranteed final four.
>> I would like to align with
Terry because I really want to
go up against him in the final
two.
If, further down the line, we
can make a deal...
>> It's got to be tonight.
It's got to be tonight with
Sally.
>> If we do remove Aras, then no
one will be able to beat Terry,
but then on the other point,
Aras is more of a threat than
Terry because he'd be much
harder to beat in the final two.
There's no clear-cut way for me
to go right now.
I'm really-- I'm still kind of
confused in my mind.
>> Terry, he's trying to win
every immunity challenge.
You mean to tell me you have an
ace in the hole and you're gonna
just hand that over, because
you're such a nice person, to
somebody else?
Come on, give me a break.
I mean, I'll be surprised.
He may do it and if he does,
that will go down as the worst
move in Survivor history because
then he has to win every single
challenge.
But, hey, I've seen crazier
things happen, so we'll see
tonight.
>> This is our fire, our life,
our journey together.
We're so blessed.
>> No answer?
>> No answer.
She's into her fire thing, but
she can't make a decision and
I'm like, "Make a freaking
decision."
If Courtney does not sway
tonight, I may or may not give
the immunity idol to Sally.
If it has to come into play, it
will.
I feel a little bit of risk
hanging it out there, but if I
come away tonight with the
numbers, then I can sit back and
don't have to win another
immunity challenge until the
final three.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the first member of our jury--
Austin, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
(laughter)
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Okay, today's
immunity challenge.
You were given a very simple
option-- participate or feast--
and no sooner did I get
"cheeseburger" out of my mouth,
five of you guys are like, "I'm
eating, I'm eating, I'm eating."
Shane, worried at all that that
bold of a move could come back
to haunt you?
>> First of all, I just would
like to say I over-performed at
the challenge today.
I got almost two cheeseburgers
down with nine fries and almost
an entire glass of Coke, but
there was a part of me that
regretted doing that.
There was part of me that felt
like I, for the team, needed to
show up and try to get immunity
away from Terry because it's
going to be very difficult, but
I also know that I don't feel
in my gut of guts that I needed
to get immunity today, and I
was-- I'm starving.
>> PROBST: Sally, got to be a
little frustrating because...
>> It's so frustrating.
I mean, the people who are
confident in this game get to be
confident and, you know what, if
they're secure in that, more
power to them.
I mean, I didn't for one second
consider eating that
cheeseburger today.
It was the easiest meal that I
have had to pass up out here
just because I needed that
immunity today.
>> PROBST: Aras, you had to feel
a little irritated that the
responsibility to win it for
Casaya came down to one guy.
>> Yeah, that was a little bit
disappointing of the Casaya
folk, whose heads could possibly
be on the chopping block if a
hidden immunity idol gets
played.
My head is definitely one of
those, but more so than that,
it's a strategy.
The quicker that we can get
Terry's immunity necklace,
which-- I call it Terry's 'cause
he's the only one who's worn it
so far-- off of his neck, the
quicker that we can get into our
strategy.
We didn't, it's over, and so now
the lay of the land is a lot
less safe for myself, but it is
what it is.
>> PROBST: Shane, is it talked
about, Terry's dominance?
>> Yeah, it's absolutely
apparent, but it's going to take
him six immunities in a row to
win.
I don't think it can be done.
If there's anyone that can do
it, it's Terry.
The guy is a 47-year-old beast
and we as a group can't really
afford to be eating
cheeseburgers after today.
>> But, regardless, I'm going to
continue winning immunities
whether they like it or not...
>> Here we go.
>> ...and my target isn't going
to get any bigger.
If I had five of these in my
back pocket, I'd be out there
competing, especially against
Aras 'cause he's a bad dude and
I want to go out there and beat
him.
>> PROBST: Danielle, Terry said
"I'm gonna keep winning them."
You mumbled "Here we go again."
>> 'Cause he always talks about
how he's so competitive and he's
so great at everything and it's
all about Terry, Terry, Terry,
but power to him for being as
confident and cocky as he is,
but...
>> PROBST: I just think it's an
interesting comment coming from
you, seeing how confident you
were today and how cocky the six
of you have been for the last
several Tribals.
>> Yeah, but I don't think we're
coming off as strongly as Terry
does.
He's a super competitive guy.
I'm not knocking that and I'm
very competitive as well and...
>> PROBST: Is that part of the
problem-- that you can't beat
him and it frustrates you?
>> I mean, it is frustrating,
but there's going to be a
challenge where Terry can't win.
I mean, if he keeps winning
every single one, God bless him.
>> PROBST: Cirie, five of the
eight of you have now been to
Exile Island, have now had a
chance to look for the hidden
immunity idol.
Are people speculating if it's
been found?
>> There's, like, 15 million
different stories.
It's here, there it is, they
don't have it, they have it.
I think everyone here just wants
it out.
If you have it tonight, here's
your chance.
>> I don't want it played
tonight because if it's played
tonight, it's me most likely
walking down that corridor, so
let it play on a night where I
have the immunity necklace.
That's my thought.
>> PROBST: Okay, Terry once
again has the immunity necklace.
As always, it's yours to assign
to somebody else if you want.
>> I'm keeping it.
>> PROBST: Okay, if the hidden
immunity idol comes into play,
we will know after the vote.
It is time to vote.
Sally, you're up.
>> (clicking tongue): I'm kind
of sick of the six of you, so
one at a time.
>> Just strategy, nothing
personal.
Hope you have the idol.
>> You're still the number one
threat, buddy.
>> You're a great player in this
game and too much of a threat.
So sorry.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Sally.
Sally.
Two votes Sally.
Aras.
Two votes Sally, two votes Aras.
Sally.
That's three votes Sally, two
votes Aras.
Sally.
Four votes Sally, two votes
Aras.
Ninth person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island: Sally.
That's enough votes.
Unless you have the immunity
idol, you need to bring me your
torch.
Sally, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, at this point, the game
seems pretty clear: six former
Casaya against Terry.
Terry says he's going to keep
winning immunity, Casaya says he
won't.
Either way, going to be fun to
watch.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, Bruce is in big
trouble.
>> Oh, God.
>> PROBST: Terry waits for
things to fall apart...
>> These guys are going to have
to turn on one another and I
hope I'm the fly on the wall.
>> PROBST: ...and he doesn't
have to wait long.
>> Courtney, chill out, dude.
>> Don't take everything so
personal!
>> A lunatic.
>> Everyone is in big trouble
'cause I'm turning the whole
game.
>> I am not disappointed that
Terry didn't give me the hidden
immunity idol.
He's got a huge uphill battle
ahead of him.
I'm disappointed I can't be
there fighting in the trenches
beside him, but I found so much
inner strength and I'll take
that with me, and I learned a
lot about myself in all this.
You know, I fought hard and I