>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> We need to talk.
>> PROBST: At La Mina...
...Dan brought Ruth Marie into
the men's alliance, and Sally
knew she was in trouble.
>> All I can do right now is
keep working hard and prove
myself valuable.
>> PROBST: At the Reward
Challenge...
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: ...the tribes played
for a fully stocked bathroom.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: Go!
Reward at stake.
Losers sending somebody to Exile
Island.
Casaya wins rewards.
(cheering and whooping)
Shane, who's it going to be?
>> Terry.
>> PROBST: And Terry was
banished to Exile Island.
When Casaya returned to camp...
>> Beautiful!
>> PROBST: ...there was some
conflict over how to use their
reward.
>> My vote is to use the
bathroom for firewood, just
keeping things dry.
>> Anyone mind if I break in
the Dumpster?
>> Use the bathroom to keep the
wood dry.
Bobby just frustrates me.
I can't stand the fact that he's
not a gentleman.
>> I feel about ten pounds
lighter.
(groan)
>> PROBST: On Exile Island,
Terry deciphered the clues...
>> Why they chose you to be the
first one out here.
>> PROBST: ...and found the
hidden immunity idol.
(whooping)
>> Beautiful.
"This talisman can be used to
keep you safe from the vote
at Tribal Council."
All right!
>> PROBST: Back at Casaya, the
alliance of four continued to
crumble.
>> For you to say it like that,
that's messed up.
>> And everybody here won't tell
you because they're afraid to
tell you the truth!
>> What are you talking about?
>> This foursome is like some
psychotic joke.
>> PROBST: Terry rejoined La
Mina at the immunity challenge.
Survivors ready? Go!
And Sally made a strong showing.
>> Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
>> PROBST: Sally running across
the beam.
But it was Casaya who took home
their second straight immunity.
Casaya wins immunity!
>> Yeah, buddy.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Though Sally was next
in line to be voted off...
>> It's a shame to pack up my
stuff and leave here with so
much left to offer this tribe.
>> PROBST: ...Austin made a bid
to keep her.
>> We got to have our strongest
team.
>> PROBST: Dan reminded his
tribe of their pact with Ruth
Marie.
>> We had an understanding to go
to the final five, and to change
horses midstream is a big
mistake.
It's crazy.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, the men chose strength
over their alliance as Ruth
Marie was voted out.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
(birds singing)
>> Pretty proud moment for me to
be the last girl standing on
this tribe.
It's a very... how many women
have left.
>> At Tribal Council last night,
Ruth Marie went home.
I was a little disappointed in
that decision, but Nick, Austin
and Terry said that Ruth Marie
just couldn't hold her weight in
the challenges and that they
wanted to switch over to Sally.
>> I miss Ruthy already.
>> I do...
I was just going to say that.
>> Every day that I spent with
her, I was more and more amazed.
>> Yeah, I'm really going to
miss her.
>> Ruth Marie ended up getting
the votes and was sent home, and
I am telling you, I have never
felt so good in my whole life.
>> That water is disgusting.
>> Coming in here and feeling
kind of like the underdog and
the outsider right off the bat,
and the fact that the four men,
who have a very tight alliance,
made a decision that I was
valuable enough to keep around
felt pretty darn good.
>> The game plan this morning is
to get some water boiled so we
have water to drink, stay
hydrated.
>> I'm going to be designing a
Zen rock garden.
Um, just kind of bring kind of a
Zen beauty to this place, 'cause
it lacks it inside the
campground and inside some of
the people's souls.
>> It's like we never have an
easy fire day.
>> It's just hard to understand.
I mean, doing all the principles
and making a fire perfectly.
>> I know.
It's just wet wood.
>> I don't know what Bruce is
doing over there.
>> He's doing his rock garden
thing.
>> While we were making the
fire, Bruce built a rock garden.
It was just a question of
whether it was the appropriate
thing to build at the time.
>> It's dire straits right now
with the fire.
>> Bruce, I've gotten firewood.
You got to understand, this is
a really tough fire right now,
okay?
You made your rock garden.
No one went complaining.
I'm-I'm working on this.
I'm doing...
I'm working as a team, okay?
I definitely shouldn't have
yelled at Bruce, and I felt bad
about that.
It was just a matter of whether
or not the tribe needed a rock
garden or a fire.
When we're in the situation,
there's got to be priorities.
>> You attacked my character.
When you do that...
>> How did I attack your
character?
>> When you... when you just say
that was nothing over there.
You don't have no idea why I'm
building my rock garden.
>> When I said that was nothing?
>> The rock garden.
>> I didn't say anything was
nothing.
>> You come back with a
childish...
That was childish to come back
with.
>> So, you're...
Hold on, hold on.
You're calling me childish?
>> No, that remark was.
I said, "The childish remark."
>> Okay.
There was no disrespecting.
>> If you can see...
I see where you're coming from.
Just try to see where I'm
coming from.
I wasn't trying to disrespect
you.
>> I know you're-you're the
master of the fire.
>> No, no, no, no. Hold on.
Hey...
>> That's why we...
>> It's all about communication,
Bruce.
>> Well, it is.
>> We're in a tough situation.
>> But don't come back... you
know...
>> So, Bruce, if you could get
some of that good wood...
>> Okay.
>> ...that's what we need right
now.
>> Okay, give me my machete.
>> There it is.
I'm the youngest person in this
tribe, and sometimes I feel like
I'm the oldest one in this
tribe.
Maybe I need kind of a little
bit of a break, a little bit of
calmness, so, to be perfectly
honest, I kind of want to go to
Exile Island.
>> PROBST: Casaya, La Mina,
come on in!
>> PROBST: Casaya, getting your
first look at the new La Mina
tribe.
Ruth Marie voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Okay, you are going
to transport rice, beans and
fish from a boat to the shore.
You will designate one tribe
member to be your retriever.
On my go, they'll race out,
retrieve one item, bring it
back to shore.
The rest of you will be lined up
like an assembly line.
You'll toss the item from one
person to the next.
When you reach the last person,
they'll toss it in the
appropriate bin.
The retriever goes back out,
gets another item.
First, you'll collect a bag of
rice, then you'll collect a bag
of beans, then you get to the
fish.
The fish are big.
And when you get to the end of
the line, the last person has to
chop the head and the tail off
the fish, throw the body in the
bin.
Two rules: if you throw an item
and the other person drops it,
you're responsible to get the
item, come back to your mat and
throw it again.
Second rule-- swapping positions
is fine.
You just need to tag out.
First tribe to get all their
items in the appropriate bins
wins reward.
Winning tribe gets it all.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: You get all of your
rice.
You get all of your beans.
You get all of your very large
fish, and to go along with it,
some spices for the fish, some
wine...
(gasping)
>> PROBST: ...and some cooking
oil.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: For the losers, not
all bad news.
You will not go home
empty-handed.
The losing tribe will take back
with them either their rice or
their beans.
In addition, one member from the
losing tribe will be sent
to Exile Island.
Big enough stakes?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Casaya, you have two
extra members.
Sitting two people out.
Who is it going to be?
>> It's going to be the two
young girls.
>> PROBST: Courtney and Danielle
will sit it out.
Take a spot, we'll get started.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
>> Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
>> Get it here! Get it here!
>> PROBST: Austin and Aras
coming back with bags right
away.
>> One motion, one motion.
>> Yeah, let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
>> Come on, Dan-O let's go.
>> PROBST: Casaya has their
first bag.
>> Go, baby, go!
>> Go!
>> PROBST: La Mina has their
first bag.
>> Come on, Aras.
Breathe, baby!
>> Come on, Aras. You got it!
You got it! You got it!
>> Swap out with me.
>> One motion! One motion!
>> PROBST: Casaya, a bit of a
lead.
Go, Casaya!
>> Okay, we got to switch.
>> PROBST: Go, La Mina!
>> Go! Come on, let's go.
>> Come on, Shaney.
>> PROBST: We switched out
retrievers-- Nick and Shane.
>> Come on, let's go.
>> PROBST: And to the fish.
These are going to be harder to
handle.
(grunts)
>> Go! Let's go!
>> PROBST: Cirie with a good
catch for Casaya.
Oh, Cirie, you got to get it!
>> Let's go! Let's go!
Come on, take your time.
>> PROBST: If you throw it and
they drop it, you have to go
get it.
Look at La Mina moving!
>> Let's go.
>> Come on, let's go.
>> Come on, Bobby!
>> PROBST: Bruce has it.
Got to chop the head and the
tail and get it in the bin.
(grunting)
Both guys whacking at it.
Go, La Mina!
Bruce slowing down on the
chopping.
>> Bruce.
>> PROBST: Watch your fingers.
Bruce really falling behind.
La Mina with the lead now.
Austin with a good catch.
Dan with a good catch.
(Bruce grunting)
Bruce really having trouble.
(grunts)
>> PROBST: Terry with a nice
grab.
Go!
You can switch out!
Shane in the water.
Go, La Mina!
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Got to get eight
total.
Reward at stake.
Losers sending somebody to Exile
Island.
>> Come on, Cirie!
>> PROBST: Oh, nice catch by
Cirie.
(overlapping shouting)
Bruce can't handle it.
>> Go, go, get it, get it!
>> Bruce, easy.
>> You need to get closer.
>> PROBST: Bobby, Bobby's got
it.
La Mina with a big lead now.
Bobby's got to get the head
and the tail off.
>> Power, Bobby! Power, Bobby!
>> PROBST: Look at that.
Go, Casaya!
Go, La Mina!
La Mina with a one-fish lead
still.
Casaya making up some ground.
La Mina working together well.
>> Go, Sal...
>> PROBST: Sally can't handle
it.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> PROBST: Bobby's got it.
La Mina really having trouble.
Dan's got to come back and toss
it again.
Bobby making quick work of the
fish.
Go!
>> Oh, come on, Sal.
Come on, Sal.
>> PROBST: Dan and Sally running
into a snafu.
>> Go, Sal.
There you go, Sal.
There you go.
>> PROBST: Now they've got it.
Terry makes a great catch for La
Mina.
Bruce, with a bad toss.
>> Good catch, Bobby.
>> PROBST: There's a good catch.
You're good.
Bobby making quick work of the
fish.
Casaya pulling ahead.
Go, Casaya!
Go, La Mina!
We are tied, six-six.
Got to get eight total.
Shane falls down.
>> Smaller, smaller.
>> PROBST: A lot of reward at
stake.
>> Smaller, smaller.
>> Underhand, underhand.
There you go.
>> PROBST: Bobby's got it.
>> Come on, Bobby!
>> PROBST: Bobby's been
fantastic with the knife.
Go, Casaya!
>> Switch!
>> PROBST: Casaya switched out
again.
Terry trying to catch up.
Go, La Mina!
We're tied, seven-seven.
This is the last fish.
Casaya with the lead.
Shane with a good catch.
Cirie with a catch.
La Mina, gotta pick it up!
>> Let's go! Come on now!
>> PROBST: Bruce to Bobby.
This could be it!
>> You got this, Bobby.
>> PROBST: Get it in the bin.
>> Get the head off.
Hurry, Bob!
Casaya! Wins reward!
>> That was awesome.
>> Bobby! Yo, baby!
Tonight we eat!
>> PROBST: Once again, another
very close challenge, but Casaya
continues their winning streak--
four challenges in a row.
La Mina, first you have a choice
to make.
Do you want the rice or do you
want the beans?
>> Beans.
Now, Casaya, you have a choice
to make.
Because La Mina lost, one person
is going to Exile Island; you as
the winning tribe are going to
decide who that will be.
>> Just out of respect, it's
going to be Terry.
>> PROBST: Terry.
Terry, you'll return to the next
immunity challenge.
You will compete with your
tribe in that.
Head on out.
Casaya, congratulations.
You got some eating to do
tonight.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff.
Head on back.
>> Oh, my God.
(thunder crashes)
>> Damn!
>> When we returned from reward
challenge-- ta-da!-- and
there's a lake.
>> This is a nightmare.
>> This is the biggest joke.
>> Total nightmare.
>> Our best reward today by far,
and we come home to a swamp.
No fire.
>> We have rice, we have beans,
we have wine and we have a ton
of fish, but we can't cook it.
Everything is wet.
We don't have any dry wood for
fire.
>> Straight raw, like sushi.
>> Of course.
>> It has to be almost a hundred
pounds of fish that we have
here, and we're just cutting
it up and eating it as
sashimi, raw fish, sushi.
>> This is cool for us to eat
this like this, right?
Ooh! I've never eaten raw fish.
I hope I don't wake up in the
morning with some kind of
sickness or something.
But they say it's okay to eat.
>> You never had sushi?
>> No.
>> What?
>> Excuse me.
>> Kill me.
>> No, no. I'm just shocked and
awed 'cause I eat it all the
time.
>> Cheers, salut.
Even though we've lost our home,
we've won a great little prize.
>> This is a tough situation.
It's two steps forward, three
steps back.
But I'm happy that we won.
We're bonding in our weird
Casaya strange-fish way.
>> Cheers, guys.
>> Yeah.
>> We made way too much, I
think.
>> Mmm.
>> We had a reward challenge and
the winner took all the spoils.
And guess who won?
Casaya, yet again.
They walked away with fish,
beans, rice.
We walked away with beans.
>> You guys gonna go in for
seconds?
>> Go for it.
>> You sure?
>> Yeah, take all you want.
There's more than enough.
>> But we're, of course,
absolutely jubilant to be
able to have food.
>> I feel nausea setting in.
>> I felt it as soon as I
stopped eating.
I'm just thinking it'll pass
within 20, 30 minutes.
(exhales)
>> How you feeling?
>> Not so hot.
It's already working it's way
through me.
My body's not responding too
well to putting the beans in the
system.
Nick and I are experiencing
a little bit of nausea.
Guess my system just wasn't
quite ready for some food.
>> I guess, you know, your
digestive system probably takes
a break when you're not eating.
I want this feeling in my
stomach to go away, Dan.
>> How are you doing?
>> Well, I was feeling better...
but I feel my stomach rumbling
again.
>> I have to go, too, dude.
Do you?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, God, I got to go again.
God. This sucks.
>> You know what? We probably
didn't cook them enough.
>> Hey, Nick.
>> Hey.
>> How you doing, bud.
>> You guys do not want to know
the details of that excursion.
>> You have both ends going?
>> Yeah.
>> That stuff just wrecked me.
That was just gross.
>> How you doing, brother?
>> No doubt I'm going to have
to go again in about five
minutes.
>> I threw up, too.
>> Oh, you threw up, too?
>> Yeah.
>> I wish I could do that.
>> The beans we ate got myself
as well as Austin really sick.
Gastrointestinal details that
probably shouldn't be discussed
at this time.
>> Well, I got to go again.
>> I got to go right now, dude.
(thunder crashes)
>> Yeah.
>> They just do whatever they
want to do.
They always, they don't think of
other people first.
>> I hear ya... (hiccups)
>> There's so much to do, I
don't know where to begin.
That's gross.
I just feel like everything's
trashed.
Luckily, last night, the
rained stopped, so the lake
didn't go into our shelter.
And I don't know what happened
to Bruce and Bobby.
Apparently they slept in the
bathroom or something.
I can't wait to hear that story.
>> I didn't see it.
If they did that, that is so
wrong.
Like seriously... that's so not
right.
(laughs)
>> I'll get it.
I got to Casa de Charmin to get
some soap, and there's Bruce
folded over, I mean literally
folded in half, and there at his
feet-- hmm?-- the empty bottle
of wine.
>> I just threw it away.
>> I would have to be dead and
someone would have to pour it
down my throat for me to drink
the last bottle of wine that we
as a tribe won.
>> What happened to that last
bottle of wine?
>> You drank it?
>> Yeah.
>> You and Bruce, or just you?
>> I ended up sharing it with
him, but I thought...
I didn't think I had any place
to sleep...
>> You drank it yourself?
>> Yeah, that's what my plan
was, and then I went in there...
gave him some.
>> How do you feel about that?
>> You feel good about it?
>> Yeah.
>> Bobby said there was no room
in the shelter, but there was
plenty of room.
It was really bad judgment of
Bobby to open the bottle of
wine and drink it.
We all worked really hard for
that.
Wine out here is like super
special.
Now none of us really trust
Bobby.
We were all supposed to
celebrate and drink that wine
together.
>> Right, and I brought it in
there, we were supposed to drink
it last night...
>> Yeah, but why would you ever
do that on your own?
>> 'Cause, you guys...
I didn't have a place to
sleep...
>> You did.
>> I didn't think I did.
Maybe I did, but when I called
out...
>> You really made a bad, bad
call.
>> I don't feel bad that I
stole your wine.
Like I feel bad that I deprived
them of wine, but I have no hard
feelings whatsoever about the
fact that you've been deprived
of wine.
Courtney definitely had a right
to be upset.
I just don't need to hear it.
I really don't care what she
thinks.
She's probably one of the two
or three most annoying people
probably in the history of the
world.
>> It's so over.
I don't have the energy for
this.
The energy I want to put on is
for the camp and that's it.
Not on this stupid stuff.
>> Something told me I was
coming back here again.
I am on Exile Island for the
second time.
There's one less thing I have
to look for right now because I
have the hidden immunity idol.
I am more independent on my own
here.
Everyone leaves me alone.
I tend to have more time for
the survival part of what I
need to do about getting
rehydrated and getting food so
that I'm strong for the
challenges.
Finally a fire.
I am really concerned about my
tribe mates.
My worst fear for La Mina right
now is they're not properly
feeding themselves and keeping
hydrated.
That's my worst fear.
>> Creepy coffin.
>> Guys, we got tree mail!
>> Tree mail!
Here we go.
"From the depths of the ocean
floor you'll hold your breath
till you can take no more.
"Paddle and swim as your body
strains.
An immunity depends on how you
use your brains."
>> Exactly not what the doctor
ordered.
Last night was one of the most
miserable experiences of my
whole life.
The beans threw my system into
a whirl, and we've got an
immunity challenge coming up
that we desperately need to win.
>> This is, like, the true
measure of what you're made of.
>> It couldn't come at a worse
time.
So going in, I definitely
would not give us the edge,
seeing as we've lost four
in a row and are going in
semi-wounded.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Terry, once
again returning from Exile
Island.
>> Hi, Terry.
>> What's up, T.D.?
(applause)
>> What's up?
>> How are you doing?
>> PROBST: Welcome back, Terry.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: First thing's first,
Courtney, give it up.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
you're going to collect skulls
from coffins sitting on the
ocean floor.
On my "go," three tribe members
will paddle out looking for
four coffins.
Each time you find a coffin,
dive down, untie the coffin,
open it.
You'll find a skull puzzle
piece.
Untie that, bring it back to
the boat.
Once you've collected all four
skull puzzle pieces, paddle
back to shore.
The two remaining tribe members
will then take those four skull
puzzle pieces and build a skull
pyramid.
The pieces will only go
together one way.
First tribe to build it
correctly and place their gold
skull on top wins immunity, is
safe from Tribal Council.
Losers, somebody going home.
Casaya, you're sitting two
people out, you cannot sit the
same people out in back-to-back
challenges.
Courtney and Danielle sat out
the last challenge.
>> We're going to sit out Cirie
and Bruce.
>> PROBST: Cirie and Bruce will
take a seat on this one.
The only thing left to find out
is if Casaya will continue to
dominate or if La Mina has found
a way to back into this game.
Take your spots.
We'll get going.
For immunity, survivors
ready?
Go!
>> Let's go! Let's go!
>> Go, Casaya!
>> PROBST: You're looking for
four coffins.
>> Paddle, paddle, paddle,
paddle, paddle!
>> PROBST: Terry trying to scope
it from above.
Terry, Danielle diving in.
Four knots to untie on each
coffin.
Danielle pops up, but no puzzle
piece.
La Mina has their first puzzle
>> Straight ahead!
>> PROBST: Looking for another
coffin.
>> Let's go, La Mina!
>> PROBST: Danielle has the
first puzzle piece for Casaya.
>> Let's go, let's go!
Come on, Casaya!
>> Paddle!
>> PROBST: La Mina's already
working on their second coffin.
Casaya, their second coffin.
Going to have to pick it up.
>> Watch your head, Dan.
Watch your head.
>> He's got it.
He's got it!
>> PROBST: La Mina has their
second puzzle piece.
>> Come on, Casaya!
>> PROBST: Casaya spending a lot
of time underwater still
looking for that second puzzle
piece.
La Mina at their third coffin.
Danielle has the second puzzle
piece for Casaya.
>> Yeah!
Here we go now!
Here we go!
>> PROBST: La Mina has their
third puzzle piece.
They do not want to go back to
Tribal Council.
>> Straight ahead.
>> PROBST: Casaya not panicking.
They found their third coffin.
>> Right underneath us, guys.
Right underneath us.
>> PROBST: La Mina at their
fourth coffin.
All three Casaya members trying
to make up some time.
La Mina with a big lead.
They have four puzzle pieces.
Could be the end of their
losing streak.
>> Come on, Casaya!
Don't give up!
Let's go!
Bonsai!
>> PROBST: Casaya with their
third puzzle piece.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: They have one piece
left.
La Mina's almost to shore.
>> Great work, guys.
>> PROBST: Drop them on the mat.
That's what you're looking for.
Here's the gold piece that goes
on top.
That's what you're building.
>> It's a triangle, it's not
square.
>> PROBST: Casaya not giving up.
>> Got it!
>> Come on, Casaya!
>> PROBST: Casaya with their
fourth puzzle piece.
They're heading back.
>> Hurry, guys!
>> Here, try putting two...
Is that it?
>> PROBST: That's not it.
>> We're still in it, Aras!
>> They can't get the puzzle!
>> PROBST: La Mina giving Casaya
a shot.
>> Come on!
>> Oh, God, this is driving me
crazy.
>> PROBST: Casaya, drop them on
the mat, on the mat!
Go, start solving it.
Shane and bobby are in this now.
They've had a lot of time to
watch La Mina and learn what
isn't working for sure.
>> It might go a little
vertical.
>> Yeah, like that.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Sally and Austin,
trying a different strategy.
One combination will work.
Nothing else will.
>> We're close.
>> PROBST: Shane and Bobby think
they're close.
>> That fits.
>> The gold skull!
>> Gold skull.
>> Gold skull, gold skull!
Gold skull!
>> That's it!
>> PROBST: La Mina has it!
La Mina wins immunity!
(cheers)
La Mina, back in the game.
Congratulations.
Nobody going home tonight.
Casaya, winning streak comes to
an end.
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody is going home from
your tribe.
Get your stuff, head on back to
camp.
>> Ow!
Son of a...
>> Guys?
Bobby, okay?
No other discussion.
Bobby goes down on the card.
>> We lost the immunity
challenge today, which forces
us to talk about voting someone
off.
The group wants Bob out.
I don't want Bob to go.
I think he's proved himself in
challenges.
>> It's got to be Bob, dude.
>> Here's the thing.
We cannot control Bruce.
We can't.
What does Bruce bring to the
table that Bob-dog doesn't
bring?
>> Nothing really.
>> Nothing.
Are we good at Bruce?
>> This is really stupid but
all right.
It's stupid, I'm telling you
it's going to end up costing
people.
>> It's not.
>> Bobby came from young guys
camp to begin with.
If we get to the merge, and
Austin and Nick are still
around, I've always been worried
about Bobby joining back up
with them.
So that was the reason why I
didn't want Bobby to make the
merge.
>> He's not going to flip.
>> I don't care.
Whatever you guys want.
>> What, you're not going to
write his name down?
>> Who?
>> Bruce.
>> I didn't say that.
>> Oh.
>> What are you babbling about?
Like, what are you talking
about?
>> Oh, I just...
I didn't hear what you said.
>> Okay, so right now you're
writing down Bruce.
The four of us are all writing
down Bruce.
Done deal, no problem?
That's not a problem?
>> Oh, my God!
I'm walking on eggshells as it
is.
Because initially way back, I
was told I'd be the next to go.
I'm just trying to lay low, fly
under the radar, let them kill
each other, and don't think
about me for...
(laughs)
for the vote tonight.
>> I don't know what anybody
else tells you, but you were
going tonight.
Straight up.
You were gone.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> But Bruce is now gone.
>> I know one of the things
that people are worried about
is that if we do make a merge
and we're 5-5 that I'll jump.
I'm not jumping.
>> Okay, so when we get to the
merge, you're not going to flop?
>> Yeah.
>> You won't?
>> Swear on my kid?
>> Yeah.
>> Swear on my kid.
>> Yeah, I won't swear on your
kid, but yeah.
>> Swear on my kid.
>> I'll swear on your kid.
>> You won't flop?
>> Right.
And you're promising me what?
>> I promise you I'm getting
you the sixth.
>> Yep.
I'm good?
>> On my kid?
>> Mm-hmm, on your kid, on
Boston.
>> Awesome.
>> All right.
>> This is my first Tribal
Council, so I'm trying to calm
myself down, and I want to keep
it low-key.
I get frustrated with Courtney
doing yoga on the Zen rock
garden.
To me, it's disgusting.
She has no respect for me or
anybody.
We've got the whole beach here
and she picks the spot I'm at.
I'd rather be on Exile Island
than be around Courtney.
>> What do you think about
Bruce?
>> I trust him.
>> 100%?
>> Yeah.
I do trust him.
I don't trust Bobby.
I don't.
Courtney, why don't we switch
this game up right now and
vote...
>> I was just thinking about-- I
was like, "At least I got my
girls."
>> ...vote off Bobby?
>> You know what I mean?
>> Let's vote off Bobby.
>> Dude, I'm just scared of--
I'm just trying...
>> I'm scared of that.
I don't like that.
Aras is putting himself, setting
himself up.
>> Aras is setting himself up so
hard-core...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...and he's going to be so
impossible to beat.
>> How about we just get Shane,
me, you-- us four vote for
Bobby.
Aras wanted Bruce gone.
I just-- I didn't feel
comfortable with that.
I wanted Bruce to stay and I
wanted Bobby to go, so I took
control and I said this is not
what I want.
Keep Bruce.
I'm telling you it's a better
decision for all of us.
It's less risky.
>> Bobby's not going to flop.
>> I just don't trust him.
>> I don't trust him either.
>> Okay, here's the deal.
I can't vote him off.
I swore on my kid that he was
the sixth.
I can't.
>> Of course he's going to swear
on your kid.
Why wouldn't he?
He knows he's getting voted off.
He's going to say anything.
>> That's-- here's the deal.
>> Bruce would stay with us more
than Bobby would.
>> I agree.
>> Well, why didn't you tell me
that an hour ago, Courtney?
You said an hour ago...
>> Don't yell at me.
>> I'm just yelling in general.
And stop with the "don't yell at
me."
I'm just-- we're talking.
You wouldn't listen to me when I
was telling you all this stuff
about Bobby.
>> Well, you were right.
>> I don't want Bobby making it
to the merge.
>> You were right.
>> You were right, you were
right.
>> You were right and now you've
been talked to and changed your
mind.
You were right from the
beginning.
>> I mean, honestly.
>> Everyone's out of their mind.
There's nothing I can do.
I told everybody initially that
Bobby should go and then they
all freaked out and said
nothing.
They're like women, you know
what I mean, and now they're
going back to Bobby.
So it's like, you know, who
knows?
>> PROBST: Everybody has a torch
except Bruce.
There's one on the end.
Go ahead and grab it.
Approach a flame and get fire.
Fire's gone, so are you.
Shane, last time you guys were
here, I kind of felt as though
this was a tribe that was in a
bit of disarray.
Has that changed?
>> I would say that we are the
dysfunctional functional tribe.
I think when it comes to
challenges, we step up and we
know how to work together, but
this tribe can be really, really
tiring.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
what's going on at camp life.
You've had some heavy downpours.
How's the shelter holding up?
>> I ended up sleeping in the
outhouse that night.
>> PROBST: In the rain?
>> Yeah, in the outhouse.
>> With the bottle of wine.
>> I went in there just kind of
trying to get comfortable for
about an hour and all of a
sudden I hear a knock on the
door, and Bobby shows up with a
bottle of wine-- and at 2:00,
3:00 in the morning in the
freezing rain with my butt
sore-- and I said "I could use a
drink."
>> PROBST: Did anyone know,
Bobby, that you took the bottle
of wine?
Was that okay with them?
>> No, they didn't know and I
found out later that it wasn't
okay.
But the reason why Bruce and I
ended up in the outhouse is that
the spots that we had reserved
were taken and I was left to
sleep exposed to the rain.
So I was like, "All right, well,
now I got this bottle of wine
and everybody I was supposed to
share it with is asleep and my
spot's been taken, so, all
right, let me go over here and
get my drink on with my boy
Bruce."
>> PROBST: I've got to say if
I'm the other five people, I'm
looking at you and Bruce and
thinking, "You guys don't want
to be a part of this tribe?
Tribal Council is easy."
>> Oh, I agree.
It was very-- I gave them plenty
of ammunition.
You know?
I didn't think it was wrong, but
I understood people could be
disappointed.
What I apologized for wasn't the
act, but it was for the way it
made people feel if it made
people feel a certain way.
>> PROBST: Cirie, did Bobby make
a mistake?
What did Bobby do from your
point of view?
>> I think it was a huge, huge
mistake only because we all as a
group fought for the reward
challenge, and the reasoning
that he's coming up with just
doesn't sound good to me.
>> But I also feel like we're
all getting on Bob.
Bruce knew very well as well
that there was three other
people that wanted that wine.
>> I'm just as guilty and I
apologize to the group now, but
even then nobody came up to me
and said, "Bruce, you ass, you
drank that."
I'm just going with the group,
and if they made it clear it was
just horribly wrong, you could
have talked to me.
>> But, Bruce, the onus is not
on them to ask for you to
explain yourself.
I think that you're responsible
to go up to the people in the
group and to say, "Look, I made
a selfish decision and I
apologize."
I mean, to Bob's credit, he
lived up to it, said, "Yo, I did
this," but to just kind of
pretend like it didn't happen,
to shuck it off your
shoulders...
>> It wasn't even on my mind
today.
There was so much that we had to
do.
That probably was the furthest
thing from my mind, honestly.
>> PROBST: Bruce, do you feel
unappreciated?
>> Oh, yeah, at times, because
they ask for my suggestion, then
they challenge it.
I've never been challenged more
times in my life on advice that
was asked for me in over a whole
year combined with thousands of
students.
It's unbelievable.
>> But Bruce, we are not your
pupils.
All right, we're your
tribesmen, and so when you do
get challenged, you can't look
at it as some sort of ego blow,
but, no, this is a tribe
learning to work together.
>> You're completely wrong
there.
I don't think that.
I was just throwing that out.
>> I just think he just feels
like he's not getting the
respect that he deserves.
He's an older man, he's a wiser
man, he has more experience than
everybody, and I just think
sometimes he doesn't get the
respect that he deserves.
>> You know, I apologize to you
guys, and I'll tell you I'm
gonna take everything you say to
heart.
You know, if something is going
to bother me, I'll clear it up
right on the spot.
Then you guys are in for it
because you'll hear more of me
then.
You guys, I appreciate you guys.
Come on.
I will, I will.
That's, that's a promise.
>> PROBST: Before we get to the
vote, Bruce is the only one of
this tribe that's been to Exile
Island.
He could have found the hidden
immunity idol.
Whether he did, it would not
come into play until after the
vote.
Cirie, you're up.
>> Bobby, you're just too
egotistical and you're selfish.
>> Bruce, I just didn't think I
could trust you.
>> This is a throwaway vote.
It doesn't mean anything.
I'm trying to make my vote go
away.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Courtney.
Bruce.
Bobby.
One vote Bobby.
Aras.
That's one vote each for Aras,
Courtney, Bruce and Bobby.
Bruce.
Two votes Bruce.
Bobby.
Here's where we stand-- two
votes Bobby, two votes Bruce,
one vote Courtney, one vote
Aras.
One vote left.
Bobby.
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island.
Bobby, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, no doubt in my mind you
were in disarray when you walked
in here tonight, but maybe the
honesty shared here tonight
could be the answer to bringing
this group together.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, the women want
Shane out.
>> It's going to be a stealth
chop of the head, guillotine-
style.
>> PROBST: La Mina hits rock
bottom.
>> Down the hatch.
>> Ugh!
>> PROBST: A big twist could
mean salvation for one...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: ...and a Tribal
Council like never before.
>> I don't really know what to
say.
I wasn't expecting to be here
this early.
I feel like I never really got
my game off the ground.
I could have played it
differently, but the truth was I
just couldn't stomach a lot of
these jokers.
People in Casaya were bonded
together out of weakness, out of
desperation.
Courtney, Danielle and Shane
are spineless little twerps, all
of them, and just being around
them made me want to throw up.
You know, at least I don't have
to be them.
I get to be Mr. Bob Dog.