>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> If you don't win immunity, if
you don't have that silly idol
from that goofy island, you're
gone.
>> PROBST: As the last two
remaining members of La Mina,
Sally and Terry faced an uphill
battle.
>> I am totally motivated to
kick your butts at everything
that comes down the road.
>> PROBST: Before the reward
challenge...
>> Hey, Dad, it's me.
I love you so much.
>> PROBST: ...everyone got a
glimpse of their loved ones.
Win today's reward challenge,
you get to see the rest of
your video and you'll enjoy
peanut butter and jelly
sandwiches and ice-cold milk.
Go!
>> Go! Go! Go! Go!
>> PROBST: Terry, Sally, Bruce,
and Courtney swung their way to
victory.
Reward for Courtney, Terry,
Bruce, and Sally.
You're sending one person to
Exile Island.
Who is it going to be?
>> Aras.
>> PROBST: On Exile Island,
Aras's search for the idol was
futile.
>> Terry's quickness to send me
might suggest that there is no
immunity idol out here.
>> PROBST: The immunity
challenge began with a twist.
If immunity is just not that
important to you, you don't have
to take part in today's
challenge.
Instead, you can chow down.
>> Doh!
>> PROBST: Aras, Terry, and
Sally passed on the offer and
went head to head for immunity,
while the rest of the tribe
gorged themselves on
cheeseburgers.
>> Here you go.
>> PROBST: Terry wins immunity
for the third straight time!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Before Tribal
Council, the Casaya members were
unified.
>> So we go Sally six-nothing
tonight?
>> PROBST: But the threat of
Terry giving the immunity idol
to Sally made Aras vulnerable.
>> It's possible that I could
go home today.
If Sally ends up having the
hidden immunity idol, then Sally
and Terry's vote will knock
somebody out.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Terry strategically
kept the hidden immunity idol,
and his last ally, Sally, was
voted out of the tribe.
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
>> Sally voted out last night at
Tribal Council means that I'm
the only one left from La Mina.
I still have a huge target on
my back, and at the Tribal
Council, and after feeling
melancholy sitting around the
fire and having them ask me,
"Oh, is there something wrong?
You want to talk about it?"
I'm like, of course there's
something wrong, you know.
And, no, I don't want to talk
about it.
I'm bummed.
>> Come a long way, baby.
>> I know.
>> It's a good feeling.
>> I'm going to have to win
every one in from now on, at
least the next three out of four
to get to the four, and then
I've got my hidden immunity
idol.
That will get me by that, if I
I need to, to get to the final
three.
I kind of feel that once I get
to the final three, I think I've
got it over everybody here as
far as mental power and
strength.
>> Oh, no!
>> Oh, Shane!
Damn!
>> You guy, can you help me?
Grab another thing or do
something?
>> Courtney, chill out, dude!
Relax!
Don't yell at me like that!
>> I wasn't yelling.
I just wanted...
>> I know, but I didn't have
anything in my hands.
>> Relax. I'm sorry.
>> What is going to be
interesting now is the longer I
hang out, the longer I get to
see how they end up turning on
one another.
>> Ridiculous.
>> The one good thing that I had
going for me as far as the
Tribal Councils recently is I
didn't have to vote against my
tribe mates.
There wasn't any of that, where
these guys are going to have to
turn on one another.
And I hope I'm the fly on the
wall.
>> My stomach really hurts.
>> You guys both are, like...
that's horrible.
>> It's difficult just to stand.
We have to drink water.
>> I remember being so
constipated, I thought I was
having a...
>> A child?
>> No, I thought I was having
a...
>> Appendicitis?
>> That's it.
I thought I was having
appendicitis, it was that bad.
>> It's hard.
My stomach is so bloated it
hurts, and I haven't gone to the
bathroom since just before the
Panamanian village feast.
It's just-- I was blocked up and
it's very, very, very painful.
>> Yeah, we all have boxes with
our names on them.
>> Oh, my God!
>> "A doll represents each of
you.
It needs a bit of your hair,
your clothes, your heart.
Give it some of your personality
and you're off to a good start.
How well you've observed your
surroundings could help
rejuvenate you for a while,
but if you've lived with
blinders on, you may find
yourself in Exile."
>> Oh.
>> It's so cute.
>> We got these dolls and we're
supposed to make them in our
likeness.
They're basically almost there.
>> How fun is that?
>> I'm trying to help my doll
out here in giving her just the
right amount of curves, so she
looks more like myself.
Shane, is that about right?
(Cirie laughing)
I actually like the blouse.
>> What do you think?
Does it look like me, Cirie?
>> Oh, my God, twins.
(Cirie laughing)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, for today's
challenge, we're going to see
how well you know the people
you've been living with for the
past 25 days.
I have a series of questions.
Each of you is going to fill out
these questions and answer these
questions in private.
I'll then tally the results;
we'll get to the challenge.
You can leave your voodoo dolls,
find a spot, fill them out, and
I'll tally them up.
Okay, I've tallied the results.
Now I'm going to ask you these
questions again.
This time when I ask you the
question, you're trying to guess
whose name came up most often.
It's not necessarily who you
voted for.
It's who you think everybody
else voted for.
There's a difference.
Each time you get one right, you
get to chop another tribe
member's rope.
Each time you chop a rope, you
release a torch.
After three chops, the voodoo
doll will go up in flames.
That person is out of the
challenge.
The last person left standing
wins reward.
I know you want to know what
you're playing for.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: The winner of today's
challenge will leave here via
helicopter to a very nice spa.
You'll get a shower, we'll wash
those clothes, get a mud
massage.
Then you will eat chicken, beef,
fish, pork chops.
>> Ah...
>> Man.
>> PROBST: You'll spend the
night, return to camp in the
morning.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winner of today's challenge will
decide who is sent to Exile
Island.
All right, everybody has their
answer board.
First question-- it's going to
be fun-- who does the least for
the tribe?
Again, you're trying to guess
whose name came up most often
to the question "Who does the
least for the tribe?"
All right, reveal.
Courtney and Danielle say Bruce.
You're not right, take a step
back.
Bruce says Courtney.
You're not right.
Danielle is the correct answer.
Cirie, Aras, Terry, Shane all
got it right.
Take a step forward.
All right, Cirie, take the first
shot.
Who is she going to hit?
Cirie going to do the first
damage.
Terry takes his first hit.
(Terry scoffs)
Aras, you're up.
Aras heading straight to Terry.
Terry takes his second hit.
Terry now has two people to get
even with, only one hit.
With some gusto, he takes Aras
out.
This game's getting real
interesting.
Shane can put Terry out of this
or inflict some pain on someone
else.
Just like that, Terry is out of
the challenge, takes a seat on
the bench.
Can't be a big surprise for you,
coming into this challenge.
Terry not talking at all.
Next question: who never shuts
up?
Keep your answers to yourself.
Everybody reveal.
A lot of Terrys, one Bruce, but
the name you actually wrote down
the most: Courtney.
Cirie has it right, Shane has it
right.
>> Oh, wow.
>> PROBST: Take a step forward.
Shane, take your shot.
Going down to the end.
Bruce takes his first hit.
Cirie.
>> Sorry, Bruce.
>> It's okay.
>> PROBST: Cirie gives Bruce his
second hit.
Bruce now down to one rope left.
Next question: who mistakenly
believes they are running this
game?
This should be very interesting.
Reveal.
The correct answer: Shane.
Courtney has it right.
Aras has it right.
Shane, obvious question: news to
you?
>> I do not perceive to think
that I'm running the game.
>> PROBST: Aras, take your shot.
Clear pecking order being
established.
Bruce is out of the game.
Take a seat on the bench next to
Terry, Bruce.
Courtney, make your move.
>> I'll go for this one.
>> PROBST: Courtney gives Shane
his first hit.
That was a rough round for you,
Shane.
(Cirie snickering)
Next question: Who would you
trust with your life?
Remember, you're trying to guess
what the group thought as a
whole.
Everybody reveal.
Cirie says Bruce.
Cirie did not vote for herself.
That's too bad.
"Cirie" was the right answer.
Aras is the only one that got it
right.
How does that feel, Cirie?
>> Thanks, guys.
(giggling)
>> PROBST: Make your move, Aras.
Setting down.
Courtney takes her first hit.
Next question: Who would you
not trust to watch your back?
The correct answer is Terry.
Courtney has it right.
Aras has it right.
Courtney, you're up.
Danielle takes her first hit.
Aras.
Aras gives Cirie her first hit.
We are even up.
Everybody down to two ropes.
Who is the biggest poseur?
Somebody's feelings are about
to get hurt.
>> What is a poseur?
>> PROBST: Reveal.
The answer to "What is a
poseur?" is you.
"Courtney" was the right answer.
Aras is the only one who got it
right.
Aras, take your hit.
Danielle now down to her last
rope.
Next question: Who is the
moodiest?
The correct answer: Shane.
Courtney got it right, and
Aras, again, got it right.
Courtney, you're up.
Shane takes his second hit.
>> You're the only one that's
hit me twice.
Your life is changing.
>> PROBST: Except for the fact
you aren't really running the
game.
>> No, I'm talking about
Courtney.
You're in the wrong team.
>> Give me a break, dude.
We're playing a game.
>> A helicopter game with a spa
to boot.
>> Come on, Bruce, please.
>> Why would you hit me twice?
>> 'Cause I didn't know...
>> Guys, guys, let's rise above
it.
This game is meant to splinter
us.
Rise above it. Come on now.
>> Yeah, it's meant to splinter
you guys.
Come on.
>> PROBST: Aras, take your hit.
>> Danielle, I love you, but I
you know you can't get me back.
>> PROBST: Danielle is out.
Take a seat on the bench with
Bruce and Terry.
Cirie, Courtney, Aras, two ropes
left.
Shane down to his last rope.
Next question: Who most easily
succumbs to intimidation?
Courtney, at the last minute,
you changed yours.
What did you have before that?
>> Myself.
>> PROBST: You were right the
first time.
Courtney is the right answer.
Shane got it right.
>> Yeah, I wonder who he's going
to hit.
>> Who do you think I'm going
to hit?
>> PROBST: Shane and Courtney
down to their last ropes.
Cirie and Aras still with two.
Who is the most annoying person
out here?
(Cirie snickering)
Everybody says Courtney except
Courtney.
Obviously, you're surprised.
>> By being the right answer
for everything? Yeah.
(Cirie stifling giggles)
It makes me feel great.
>> PROBST: Aras, you're up.
And with that, Courtney takes
her third hit.
>> Horrible.
>> PROBST: Courtney's out of the
game and probably happy to be
out of the game.
>> Well, I'm sure I'll be the
right answer to everything else
today.
>> PROBST: Shane heads to Aras.
>> Baby doll, please don't put
me out.
Me owe you one.
>> PROBST: Shane playing
strategically.
Aras down to one rope left.
Shane down to one rope left.
Cirie, who are you going to put
out of this game?
(Cirie groans)
Come make your hit.
>> Shane, I'm sorry.
>> Why d... Why?
>> Because I promised Aras I
wouldn't hit him.
>> You did?
>> Yeah.
>> That tells me a lot, too.
>> Sorry, Shane.
>> PROBST: Cirie knocks Shane
out of the game.
>> Shane takes a seat on the
bench.
>> Cirie just like under the
radar, gets her thing.
>> Shane, come on, it's a game.
>> Don't be such a hard...
>> It's all good.
I'm just having an emotional
reaction.
>> Okay, it's all right.
>> It's all good.
I want to go on a jet and fly
and eat a sandwich.
It's all good.
>> PROBST: Here's where we
stand: Cirie has two ropes
left; Aras, you have one.
That means if Cirie gets this
right, regardless what you do,
it's over.
>> It's over. Right.
Next question: Who would never
survive on their own?
>> What do I do?
What do I do?
>> PROBST: Cirie not sure what
to do.
Takes a long time to make her
decision.
Did she get it right?
Reveal.
Aras says Terry.
Cirie says herself.
The correct answer is Cirie.
Cirie got it right.
Cirie wins this challenge.
Make your last hit.
(applauding and cheering)
>> Did you do that on purpose,
Aras?
>> Me? I don't think you could
survive a day in the wilderness.
>> Sorry, Aras.
>> PROBST: And with that, Cirie
wins her first challenge.
>> Yay!
>> Good job, Cirie.
(Cirie exhales sharply)
>> PROBST: Nicely done.
>> Thank you, thank you.
>> PROBST: All right, first
decision you have to make: Who
are you sending to Exile Island?
>> Oh, I can't send... 'cause
I... Terry, sorry.
>> PROBST: Terry, for a third
time, going back to Exile
Island.
Did you expect that?
>> I've come to expect all bad
things for right now, Jeff,
until, uh, something changes.
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: Head on out, Terry.
The boat will pick you up.
All right, Cirie, so, helicopter
ride, spa, massage, clean
clothes, take a shower, a lot of
food.
You're bringing two people with
you...
(Cirie sighs)
>> PROBST: ...which means you
are leaving three people behind.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: You've already sent
one person to Exile.
Who's the first person?
Shane is on his knees begging.
>> Oh, Cirie!
>> I promised Aras since day
one.
I'm sorry!
>> PROBST: Aras, head over.
>> I promised.
I gotta keep a promise.
Oh...
>> PROBST: One more person going
with you.
The other three going back to
Gitanos camp.
>> First.
>> We talked about this, Cirie.
We already talked about this.
>> She promised.
>> We did, Shane, but it was
after Danielle.
>> PROBST: Danielle is your
choice?
>> I'm sorry. Yes.
Sorry, Shane, I'm sorry.
>> You are sorry.
Devastating.
>> Aras promised me since day
one, day one, if he ever won, he
would take me.
>> I'm not worried about Aras.
>> So, I mean...
>> I'm worried about the
Danielle call.
I think that you made the wrong
call.
>> Okay.
>> Thanks.
>> Have fun.
>> PROBST: All right, guys,
helicopter waiting for you down
on the beach.
Bruce, Courtney, Shane, rough
afternoon.
I got nothing to make it any
better.
Get your stuff, head on back to
camp.
>> This is amazing!
>> We're doing it!
We're in a helicopter!
>> Oh, yeah.
(laughter)
>> Look at this.
>> Oh... my... God!
>> Ha-ha.
>> This is going to be the best
night of my life.
>> Oh, my God
Honestly, I'm so happy.
>> I'm not kidding.
>> I have never been in a
helicopter before.
It's almost like I was alone
flying above this place,
getting to see all of this
stuff that I would never in a
lifetime... on my own be able to
see.
Oh... my... God!
I picked Aras and Danielle
because they were the people
that I thought I would have the
most fun with.
But this could potentially be,
like, a fatal move for me.
I'm probably public enemy #1
now because I didn't take the
people who are back at camp.
>> What is on this plate?!
God, I'm so happy!
(Cirie chuckling)
I'm going to lean back.
You guys, relax, relax.
There's so much food.
>> Mmm...
>> I had fun at that challenge.
I laughed so much.
>> I did, too, but it wasn't
fun in the end.
Man, they put Courtney as the
most annoying.
Wow.
>> She got that, too?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> She and Cirie did.
She cleaned up today.
>> You should have seen her
face.
>> That's why I couldn't stop
laughing 'cause it was so funny.
I mean, I would be kind of
pissed if my tribe members
thought that I was the most
annoying.
(stifled laughter)
Oh, my gosh.
I would have felt the same way.
>> I've always thought that me,
Aras, and Cirie were tight in a
three-way thing, and today, I
don't know.
Like, I got to ask myself
where Cirie is with Danielle.
And so, I was pretty shocked
that she didn't pick me today,
for sure.
>> Well, that was fun.
You get to know where you stand.
>> I had no idea Danielle and
Cirie were that close.
>> I don't care about that.
I care about the game.
And what you said about me.
>> You do?
>> Are you kidding?
Can you just think for a second
how that would make you feel?
I'm sure you didn't pay
attention to how many answers I
was the answer to, but...
>> I think you're also
personalizing a lot of it.
>> How can I not be...
opinion about me?
>> No, but some of the questions
were stupid.
Who is the most annoying?
That one might not be fun,
but...
>> It's hurtful.
I just got, like, I was so
happy to be here, like,
yesterday.
Now I'm, like...
I don't want to be here.
I'm going to have to live with
this for the rest of my life.
>> Courtney destroyed herself
today.
I mean, she takes a lot of stuff
personally, anyway, and just to
hear the, like, some of the
answers to what the tribe thinks
about her is just, I think
really got her in an all-time
low.
(coughing)
You know, the common voice of
the tribe was heard today, you
know?
She got a lot of bombs dropped
on her today, so it's gonna be
very interesting to see how she
handles herself for the next few
days.
>> Yeah, Bud?
>> Bruce has been in pain for
the last few days, and it
started to really sort of double
and triple up, I think.
>> I've had so many weird
injuries.
Tons of horrible injuries and
This is one of the most painful.
But... it's part of the game.
>> His stomach has been
bothering him for the last ten
to 12 days, and it's been a
matter of him not being able,
really, to go to the bathroom.
And at times, Bruce can tend to
be overdramatic, but there was
nothing overdramatic about what
was happening.
He was in a lot of pain.
(groans)
>> My whole back, all my
stomach, everything, my whole
inter... hurts so bad every
second.
And this, the pain is just
increasing.
So painful.
>> Yo, you got to get better
'cause we need you.
(groaning)
>> I'm just concerned 'cause
it's escalating so fast.
(groans)
(Cirie moans)
>> Ooh!
Thank you, God, for letting
me get this one.
If I don't win anything else,
thank you, God. Whoo!
We got a mud massage.
That is wonderful.
It was like "Lifetimes of the
Rich & Famous."
I felt like Robin Leach.
Well, Danielle, is this
something for your first
massage?
>> Oh, good.
The man that gave me a massage
was pretty rough 'cause I've
never had a professional massage
done, but I usually like to be
massaged a little bit easier.
Aah!
>> Danielle picked the guy.
>> Oh, boy.
>> She figured he'd have
stronger hands, and he did.
>> Holy snakies.
>> Wow. Oh, my gosh.
>> Do I have another stomach?
(laughter)
That's it.
Maybe one more bite.
>> Today is almost like I'm
starting over.
If I'm out of the game because
of this, at least I got to do
this before I went because
this is great.
>> I think that game officially
pointed out the immaturity of
our group.
Courtney, her and Shane, man,
they are so similar.
>> They are.
>> She has a serious crush on
him, I think.
>> A total crush on him.
>> And the thing is with
Courtney, is she just wants to
be wanted.
Like, that's her psychological
pattern, and so she loves it
when Shane engages her in those
arguments about her being
passive-aggressive.
Even though she'll, like, walk
away and be angry, she knows
that there's going to be a
makeup point.
>> I can imagine the arguments
they're going to have tonight--
Courtney and Shane.
You know they've been arguing
since they got back.
>> Poor Bruce, he's right there
smack-dab in the middle.
>> And he's hurting.
>> Poor Bruce.
>> I'm going to be so not liked
tomorrow.
>> I like you.
>> I love you.
(laughter)
(Bruce groaning)
(groaning)
>> Uh-oh.
>> It's been doubling and
escalating so fast since I got
back.
(groans)
>> Can I sing you a song.
Will that help?
>> No.
It's going to be okay.
♪ Just take me away... ♪
>> Bruce had really horrible
stomach pains.
He's had pains for about four
days now, and it just got
really unbearable for him.
And I went in there, was trying
to calm him down 'cause he
was just like, literally like
writhing and convulsing in
pain, and he was just begging
for the medics to get here, so
the medic had to be called.
>> I don't want to quit.
>> Huh?
I just want to get well.
(groans)
(motor rumbling)
>> Aw...
>> Bruce?
(Bruce groans)
>> Hi.
>> Hi. How you doing?
>> It gets worse; it just
escalates so bad.
(groans)
>> Talk to me.
Whereabouts is the pain?
>> All over my back and stomach
but... (groans)
It's just getting worse.
>> Bruce, are you allergic to
anything?
>> No, injuries-- tons of them.
(Bruce groans)
>> Brain has been hurting for
hours.
Oh, God...
Oh, God, it hurts so much.
>> All right, lift your head up
for a minute.
Just going to unbutton your
shirt here.
>> It's not fair.
(Bruce yells)
>> Okay...
>> Don't, don't, don't.
>> (groaning): All right.
Aah, I've been in pain so long.
(panting)
Don't miss.
(groaning)
>> I can't touch...
Oh, give me some relief, please.
>> What I want you to do is hold
this to your mouth and breathe
in and out, just nice smooth
breaths.
(coughs, groans)
>> That's it.
>> My stomach hurts so much--
it's increasing.
>> Ow, ow...
>> I'm going to need you guys to
help me carry the stretcher.
I'm just going to go out to the
boat and head back to base camp
and I'll reassess him there.
I think we've got his pain under
control, and all his vital
signs...
>> Okay. Did you give him a
shot?
>> Uh, do we need to do this
right this second?
>> Yes, we do.
>> Bruce, what I'm gonna get you
to do...
You move towards me.
I'm not gonna move you.
Here, I'll give you help.
Lift that foot up.
There you go.
...so you roll back down.
(Bruce groans)
>> Just... on your side a bit
there.
Just nice and slow.
Do you want to use my hand?
>> Ow...
>> It's going to be all right,
Bruce.
(groans)
>> I'm going to pull it.
Everyone's going to follow him
all the way.
Lift up, nice and gently, that's
it.
>> Bruce, we'll see you really
soon.
>> Steady, and stop there.
(indistinct orders)
>> Love you, Bruce.
>> See you in a minute, Brucey.
(Bruce groaning)
(boat engine rumbles)
>> Back...
I would hope Bruce would
come back and finish on his own
terms, absolutely.
I don't want to have anybody,
just-- you know what I mean, be
pulled from the game because of
medical reasons.
I wouldn't feel right about it
at all.
But I think that he definitely
would feel like, um, he didn't
get to finish under his terms,
and I know that would be a hard
thing for Bruce, because Bruce
has lived a really beautiful,
whole, big, gi-normous life,
so...
No, I wish... I really hope
Bruce gets to come back.
>> Casaya totally has it out for
me.
There's been a target on my back
since the merge, so the
participation part of the reward
challenge was a joke, a waste of
time for me, but the good part
about it was the observation
time where I got to watch the
Casaya members go at it against
one another.
You know, yesterday wasn't a
total loss, and being sent here
to Exile Island gives me a
little bit more time to think
about strategy for the upcoming
two weeks.
>> Poor Brucey.
I wonder how he is today.
Yesterday was an extremely
emotional, draining day for me.
Ending the day with Bruce being
taken away was like the icing
and the cherry and the hot
fudge on top of my, uh, pretty
poo-poo day.
>> Let me ask you a question.
If I need your vote in order to
get us one person further, would
you trust me and not break my
back?
I can't have the
obsessive-compulsive, like, you
overthinking part.
>> It's-It's hard for me to say,
yes, I'll just agree with
everything that you think.
You know, obviously, it's hard
to say.
But, you know, I want to be on
your backside, and I would like
you to be on mine.
>> Okay.
>> So, we're on the same page of
what we want.
>> All right, grab that little
log right there, that skinny
one.
>> We just keep everything
between us.
>> If we don't...
>> Don't.
>> ...I'll kill you when I get
back to Hollywood.
>> (laughs): No. Great.
>> I will.
I'll drive up, and I'll kill you
in your ... little apartment.
Then I'll drive over to my club,
and that'll be it.
>> That was really nice.
I don't have a ... apartment.
>> (shouting): Well, obviously,
dude, I don't...
I've never been in your
apartment!
I don't know if it's ... or not!
It was an adjective!
>> I know.
>> Don't take everything so
personal!
>> You're just so obnoxious.
You're not funny.
>> No, I'm not obnoxious, man.
Think about it.
>> Wait, you're not...
>> Why are you so...
>> You're not...
>> ...sensitive?
Glenn Close, Sybil, bunny
boiler, Fatal Attraction--
she's so scary, man.
She's a lunatic, man, and
especially after yesterday, and
finding out that the entire
tribe thinks she's an idiot.
I mean, she is a dream to take
to the final two.
Anyone could win against her.
Anyone.
It's crazy.
She's a dream.
>> Danielle, Aras, and I-- we
get home from the reward, and,
uh, no one's there to greet us.
Oh, my God.
The tension at the camp when we
got back was so thick, I was
afraid to-to come past the palm
frond trees, because I didn't
know if, you know...
Was it safe?
>> Is that Court?
>> Welcome home.
We lost a member.
>> Shut up!
>> Bruce.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Bruce went home?
>> Yeah.
He was med-evac'd out of here.
>> So he's done?
>> Shut up.
>> I don't know.
Well, last night was just,
like...
He was super sick, then we
called medical, and then the
boat came and took him up, and I
have no idea if he's in the
game, if he's okay.
I don't know anything.
>> Wow!
>> But you guys had a great
time, I'm sure.
>> We get back to the beach,
and Bruce Factor has been
med-evac'd out of here.
Courtney, who was really
affected by the last challenge.
And finally I see Shane, and
Shane, honestly, was an animal.
>> I caught a boa constrictor.
>> He just looked like he hadn't
eaten food, had water, or seen
people in days.
>> You all right, man?
>> Yeah, no, I'm good.
>> What's going on?
>> Nothing.
>> Damn!
>> We're not good.
I don't trust her.
>> Shane, Shane...
>> She's got to come to me.
>> She will.
She'll talk to you about it.
>> I am disappointed in her in
a big way, and I am not going
out before Danielle, dude.
That bitch did nothing for 30
days.
Gets to go up yesterday.
She's done nothing but be lazy
and wait to get fed, and Cirie
takes her?
That is not right.
I have put Cirie on my back, all
300 pounds of her.
Have put her on my back.
You and I both have.
It was wrong yesterday.
It was wrong.
>> Didn't you play sports?
Didn't you have teams?
Like, you lose some, you win
some.
Get over it.
>> Listen, I'm not worried about
anybody but me now.
>> I know you're not.
>> And guess what?
Everyone is in big trouble
'cause I'm going to do whatever
it takes.
If you and Cirie don't make me
absolutely believe that it's
still the three of us...
>> Mm.
>> ...I'm turning the whole
game.
I mean, look at me, look at me.
I'm in the game now.
I'm in the game.
>> I know, and...
>> And everyone's in a big, big
problem.
>> I tried not to get into it
with Shane.
All of it was basically his
insecurity about where he
stands.
In my thinking, the last thing I
need is Shane on the loose
really changing this game up,
so just let him say his piece.
We'll get him down.
We'll calm him down.
We'll gain back his trust, and
hopefully, Cirie will peace it
with him, and we'll be all good.
>> First, as far as the game
part is concerned, I've never,
ever wavered about me, you and
Aras.
Did you see me there?
Did you see me?
"Oh, okay, it's just you and
you."
It was so hard because I know
how you felt.
Did you not think it was hard
for me to not take you after
everything?
>> Yeah, but, I... yeah.
I didn't...
I didn't know that it was...
I had no idea that you and
Danielle had the type of...
Like, I watched it, but I was
just, like...
>> That's what I'm saying.
It's not like a type of thing
like we have.
Nothing like that at all.
Shane is so hurt because he
feels like he deserved the
reward way more than Danielle.
He just thought it would be a
no-brainer.
If I won, me, him and Aras would
go.
>> Uh-uh.
>> All right.
>> Yes?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Me, Cirie and Aras are in an
alliance, officially, and will
be until we get to the four.
The whole discussion was a big
rant and was absolutely
calculated by me in order to get
ahead of Cirie and Aras
mentally, and it played exactly
the way I wanted it to.
I think, subconsciously, I
control that-that threesome for
sure.
>> I'm just cleaning, um,
Bruce's Zen garden, and I wanted
to write the words, like, "Love,
Bruce," just to send him love
right now, 'cause no matter
where he is right now, he's-he's
having a hard time.
I was going to put l-u-v, "luv
you," on this side.
>> That would be great.
>> Bruce was just go, go, go,
go, go.
That was his mentality, and I
gave him a lot of credit.
I mean, I looked at him as like
a father figure.
I mean, I really connected with
him.
You know, I said my prayers for
him last night.
I just really hope that Bruce is
okay.
Um, you know, it was...
I had, like, an eerie feeling
last night that he wasn't even
in the shelter, and I just pray
to God that everything's fine
and he's healthy.
>> He would love it.
He would love it.
>> I don't even care about the
game aspect of it.
I just want to make sure he's
okay.
So I hope we find out soon!
>> Here comes a boat.
>> Terry has a red shirt with
blue sleeves, right?
>> Yeah.
>> It's still three, whoever it
is, man.
>> Is that Terry?
>> Yeah, that's Terry.
>> It's Jeff.
>> Isn't that Probst?
>> Shut up!
>> And Probst?
>> Yeah, and Probst is with him.
>> Jeff and Terry.
Wow.
I need to go find out what this
is about.
>> PROBST: What's going on,
Aras?
>> A lot, apparently.
>> It is Terry.
Damn.
>> Well...
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: How you doing?
>> Good to see you, sir.
>> PROBST: Nice to see you.
(indistinct chatter)
Hello.
>> Hello.
>> Hi.
>> PROBST: Where's Courtney?
You heard about Bruce?
>> I haven't heard anything.
>> PROBST: I'll give you the
whole low-down.
>> I haven't heard anything.
>> PROBST: Let's do it up at
camp.
>> PROBST: Wouldn't have a...
I don't know if you guys got
seats or anywhere you can plop
it.
Okay, I know everybody wants an
update.
I have an update.
First, we got to catch Terry up.
I think everybody was pretty
clear that when we went to the
last reward challenge, Bruce
wasn't feeling very well.
Had a lot of stomach pain, was
having trouble walking.
Reward challenge ends, pain
continues.
Bruce asks for medical to come
in and check him.
Medical checks him out, runs
some tests, says you need to go
to a hospital.
And it is a good thing that he
got there when he did.
They ran some tests and found
out that his entire digestive
system-- his colon and his
bladder-- were blocked.
Nothing was coming out.
And I know everybody's concerned
about Bruce's well-being.
He's going to be okay, but he
will not return to the game as
a player.
Bruce is no longer in the
running for a million dollars.
It is now down to you six.
There will be no immunity
challenge today.
Nobody will be voted out tonight
at Tribal Council.
We're hoping that Bruce will be
back for the next Tribal Council
and continue on as a member of
the jury, but we're waiting for
approval from the doctors.
So, that's the update.
You have the afternoon off, and
the game continues on.
Make sense?
>> Sure. Thanks for coming.
>> PROBST: Sorry it was bad
news.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Later, guys.
>> Bruce is the master sensei.
You know, he'll be back.
He's a fighter.
I-I don't think any one of us
could have put up with the pain
that he put up with in the hopes
of, uh, staying in the game, and
to see him go this way is a
shame, 'cause he's a warrior, a
total warrior.
57-year-old master sensei in the
true sense.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Look for the address?
>> Shane found a piece of wood
and is calling it his
Blackberry.
>> Send.
I'm communicating with people,
not on this island.
(cuckoo clock chimes)
>> PROBST: Want to know what
you're playing for?
The survivors are in for a
surprise.
>> Yeah! Yeah!
(Cirie shrieks)
>> PROBST: And Cirie faces a
monster!
(shouts)
(grunting)