>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
After Tribal Council, Sally was
the last woman standing at
La Mina.
>> Ruth Marie ended up getting
the votes and was sent home.
And I am telling you, I have
never felt so good in my whole
life.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the tribes competed
for food and wine.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: La Mina took the
lead.
Terry with a nice grab.
Bruce really having trouble.
But Sally struggled, and Bobby
chopped his way to victory for
Casaya.
Casaya wins reward!
>> Tonight we eat!
>> PROBST: Casaya won fresh
fish, rice, beans, spices and
wine, while La Mina was left
with only a bag of beans, and
had their leader sent, once
again, to Exile Island.
>> Good luck, Terry.
(thunder crashing)
>> PROBST: Casaya returned to
find their camp underwater.
>> This is a nightmare.
>> We have a top of fish, but
we can't cook it.
Everything is wet.
>> PROBST: But even without
fire, they managed to make the
most of their reward.
>> I've never eaten raw fish.
I hope I don't wake up in the
morning with some kind of
sickness or something.
>> PROBST: At La Mina, the
tribe devoured their first
nourishment in days...
but the beans were too much
for Nick and Austin's stomachs.
>> Well, I got to go again.
>> That stuff just wrecked me.
>> PROBST: Back at Casaya,
Bobby and Bruce spent some
quality time in the outhouse.
>> Excuse me.
>> PROBST: And in the morning,
they paid the price.
>> What happened to that last
bottle of wine?
>> Someone would have to pour
it down my throat for me to
drink the last bottle of wine
that we, as a tribe, won.
>> You really made a bad, bad
call.
>> I don't feel bad that I
stole your wine.
Like, I feel bad that I deprived
them of wine, but I have no hard
feelings, whatsoever, about the
fact that you've been deprived
of wine.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
La Mina with a big lead!
...La Mina finally broke their
losing streak.
>> That's it!
>> PROBST: La Mina has it.
La Mina wins immunity!
Back at Casaya, the alliance of
Shane, Aras, Courtney and
Danielle made their decision.
>> No other discussion.
Bobby goes down on the carpet.
>> PROBST: But Aras changed the
plan.
>> We cannot control Bruce.
>> This is really stupid, but
all right.
>> PROBST: Then Danielle
changed the plan again.
>> Keep Bruce.
I'm telling you, it's a better
decision for all of us.
>> PROBST: And Shane was
irritated with his tribe's
flip-flopping.
>> Why didn't you tell me that
an hour ago, Courtney?
I told everybody, initially,
that Bobby should go, and then
they freaked out and said
nothing-- they're like women.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
the voting was erratic.
But three votes were enough to
make Bobby the fifth person
voted out of the game.
Bobby, the tribe has spoken.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
(thunder crashes, birds and
insects hoot and chitter)
>> I know Bruce is in here.
I'm not worried about it.
Listen, why do I have to
worry about anybody, homey?
>> I don't know where all this
anger is coming from.
And I don't appreciate you
directing it towards me, so can
we just talk about this
tomorrow?
Because I don't feel like
getting into a huge fight with
you.
It's not worth it.
>> I want to get out of the
alliance that I'm in with you
guys, but I can't do that
unless you guys allow me to
take my son's name back, so...
>> Why would you say that?
>> Because I don't trust that
you guys are going to make the
right decisions.
I'd rather go into the merge
a lone wolf than have to deal
with you and Courtney.
>> I don't know, like, I don't
know why you're... you have all
this anger towards me and you're
going to start bashing me now,
because you're going to go
through one of your manic,
crazy spasms.
I don't need to deal with it.
I don't want to deal with it.
I'm going to bed.
If you still feel like that
tomorrow, then bring it up
tomorrow and we'll argue
tomorrow, okay?
Because I just... I don't need
you bashing me.
>> I know, you're such a
victim, Danielle.
>> I know... I am.
(thunder rumbling)
>> Like that.
We got one, two, three, four.
(grunts, sputters)
>> Courtney had decided to
sleep on the beach last night,
so I had to catch Courtney up...
(laughing)
...on, uh, Shane's wanting to
leave their alliance.
You know, she has to know.
(laughing)
Um, so Courtney decided, well,
let's get rid of Shane.
"Wouldn't that be amazing?" is
what she said.
I'm like, "Oh, okay. Huh."
(laughing)
>> Out.
(laughing quietly)
Last night, we get back to the
shelter, and Shane has one of
his crazy, manic, psycho fits
again, and he's next.
That's the bottom line.
He's such an idiot.
I can't stand him.
>> Yeah.
>> He's such a moron.
I cannot wait to vote him off.
>> He's so getting what he
deserves.
>> He's just a lunatic.
He's lost his mind.
He's just a freak.
(whispering): "I want out of
the alliance with you and
Courtney."
And then he's saying that he
wants nothing to do with me and
Courtney.
You know, "I want out.
You guys are disorganized.
I don't like the way the Tribal
Council went down."
Well, if that's how you feel
about it, then fine.
Get out of the alliance.
You're off anyway, who cares?
See you later.
Bye.
>> This is so on the down-low.
It's going to be a stealth
chop the head off, guillotine
style.
>> It's beautiful out here.
Another beautiful day in
paradise.
I'm taking a quiet moment to
enjoy it.
I've been within 200 miles of
this spot many times,
vertically.
Good morning.
>> I feel really groggy today.
>> I'm going to get the fire
on, and then we'll warm up the
beans.
>> They taste a little better.
>> It's been a rough couple of
days.
The four guys are kind of
doing, like, a boys' club thing.
But I think it's shortsighted.
These guys think that they know
how the game works, but, like,
I'd be very surprised if the
all-man's club ended up lasting
as long as they think it would.
>> These are little minnows.
They're caught in this pond
here.
They're tiny, tiny, but they're
salty.
They're better than nothing.
They are protein.
>> I've been fantasizing about
food since day two.
I can't stop, no matter what I
do.
If we could get some food in
our stomachs, this whole game
could change.
You'd think I was diving for
friggin' chicken nuggets down
here.
I... got one.
Don't you move.
Food.
He's going down the hatch.
Boy, did he taste awful.
Ugh!
>> Hey, Nick.
>> Yeah?
As in?
>> While they were flying.
>> As in when they were flying?
You've got to be kidding me?
>> Yeah.
Three space shuttle flights, uh,
once aboard the shuttle
Endeavor, twice aboard shuttle
Discovery.
>> Oh, my God.
>> It's a dream come true, what
I wanted to do my whole life.
>> Dan, that's unbelievable.
I never thought I'd even meet
an astronaut, never mind live
with one.
I mean, the guy has looked at
Earth from space.
So he's, he's an incredible guy,
and I knew that from the start.
To learn that and how humble he
is about, um, being an astronaut
is... is pretty amazing.
>> You wouldn't believe how many
people told me I could never be
an astronaut.
I've been to orbit three times,
on space shuttles, I've done
four space walks, I've been to
space station twice.
>> Man, I need to come up with
something, 'cause I got nothing.
>> Hey, Nick, you and I, we got
nothing time, though, baby.
>> That's true.
>> Man, that's awesome though,
dude.
He actually has dined with Neil
Armstrong.
Dan Flago is a stud.
I told you from the get-go.
He's a pimp.
>> You know what, it wasn't
like hiding anything from you.
It was because I didn't want to
be, you know, the "astronaut"
guy.
I just wanted to be Dan.
We've become really good
friends, and I don't want to
keep the secret from them
anymore.
This is just another way for us
to... to bond.
>> I guess I need to come clean.
My real name is John Grisham.
>> I was going to say, yeah.
>> Sunshine again.
So happy.
>> Usually, in a normal
alliance, we could say, "Listen,
I just want to be out of this."
But I can't really do that
because I... I swore on my kid's
life that I'd stay with you
guys.
>> What, what, why are you so
upset?
>> I'm not.
Listen, I don't, I don't want to
talk about that.
I want to really, I want to ask
you guys if I can take my son's
name...
>> Done.
>> Done? Courtney?
>> I don't, you're, you're
making a mistake right now.
I don't see...
>> I'm not making a mistake.
I'm never gonna ever be beholden
to people that make decisions
based on personal feelings.
You guys voted Bobby out of
here because you, Bobby pissed
you off five days ago.
>> Negative.
>> No.
>> Okay.
>> I stuck to the original plan,
so if you want to get angry at
someone for flipping, then you
should get angry at me.
>> I did.
I got angry at Courtney.
I told... I got angry at
Courtney, got angry at...
>> You lashed out at me last
night.
>> Like, all you're doing is
lashing out at people.
>> Oh, all I do is lash out at
everyone.
>> You do.
>> It's terrible, awful.
>> You guys do nothing.
You guys do nothing.
>> Honestly, you have these,
like, outbreaks, and you just
lash out at whoever is next to
you.
And I'm sick of it, so don't...
I don't want to hear it.
Don't lash out at me again.
I don't need it.
Honestly.
I'm not here for that.
I came here to enjoy myself, not
to have people demean me.
>> I second that motion.
>> I haven't lashed out at you
in days.
>> You were horribly
disrespectful to me yesterday.
What are you mumbling about
over there?
I mean...
>> You don't even realize...
>> You don't even realize how
mean you are.
>> You just talk so down to
people, like...
>> It's funny how you two are
the only two that have a problem
with it.
>> We're the only ones who need
to say anything about it.
>> I'm done.
>> You done?
>> Set aside, it's done.
>> I need to get out of this
alliance, because I'm in it
with an idiot, and I don't want
to be with Shane.
I just don't.
I don't, I don't trust that he's
going to keep his mouth shut.
I don't respect the way he
treats other people.
And I don't want to be a part
of that.
If I have a choice, I don't want
to be a part of it.
So truth be told, I think it's
great the alliance is broken up
because it's a paper tiger.
There's no power to this
alliance anymore.
>> I don't like Courtney,
either.
But I did.
I screwed myself bad.
>> I feel like Shane just wrote
his walking papers, basically.
And unless he somehow is able
to apologize to the girls, say,
"Look, I didn't really mean it,"
I feel like that guy is going to
go home.
(screeches)
>> Ooh!
That's scary.
>> Simple.
>> That looks freaky.
That doesn't look like a fun,
like, trivia game.
>> Terry, we got tree mail.
>> Tree mail.
>> All righty, bring it on.
>> "With strength and smarts
today, we'll see, how hard
you'll compete for immunity."
>> Another immunity?
>> No, this one's huge.
>> Wow!
>> "The winners get away for a
treat you'll dig."
>> Oh, my God!
>> We have got to win.
>> "Today the stakes are high
and the reward is big."
>> Oh!
Oh, God!
>> Wow!
>> This is the sweetest thing
I've ever heard.
>> Immunity and reward.
>> That's awesome!
>> This could be immunity.
Immunity.
Let's, let's, let's pare the
numbers down today, you guys.
>> I'll die if we don't win
this.
>> We're gonna win it.
>> It is absolutely vital that
we play to win today.
We need to win this.
We need to be able to get the
numbers even before, for it
potentially go into a merge.
>> I'm not going home tonight,
you guys.
>> Let's get it done today,
guys; let's get it done.
>> One, two, three, La Mina!
>> Come on, baby.
>> If we win, five on five.
>> Strength and smarts.
>> If we lose, Sally most likely
will be gone and we're gonna be
hurting big time.
So, uh, we're totally stoked.
This, this is, this is game
seven of the World Series.
>> PROBST: La Mina, come on in!
Casaya, come on in.
La Mina, getting your first
look at the new Casaya.
Bobby voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Better believe it.
>> You bet.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Nick.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs because today's
challenge is for both reward
and immunity.
Here's how it works.
On my "go," three members from
each tribe will race out to the
field to collect puzzle pieces.
You'll go one at a time.
You'll untie it, lower it,
unhook it, bring it back.
Once you have all four pieces,
the two remaining tribe members
will use those pieces to solve
a spinning puzzle.
First tribe to solve it
correctly wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: Everything you need
to have a good afternoon and a
good, old barbecue.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: Including some toys
you're going to bring for the
children of a local Panamanian
village that will be your host.
You will have a Panamanian
barbecue: barbecued chicken,
barbecued beef, wine, beer,
soft drinks, the works.
And that's not all.
While the winners are partying,
the losers will be at Tribal
Council tonight, where somebody
will be voted out.
And as always, the winning
tribe gets to choose one member
from the losing tribe to send
to Exile Island.
The difference is, this time,
the person you send to Exile
Island will not go to Tribal
Council tonight.
That means they cannot be voted
out.
So instead of punishing
somebody, you are protecting
somebody.
Big stakes at this point in the
game.
Worth playing for?
(all agreeing)
>> PROBST: Casaya, you have one
extra member.
You're sitting somebody out.
Who is it gonna be?
>> Courtney is gonna sit out.
>> PROBST: Courtney will sit
out.
Who are gonna be the three
people for Casaya that will
gather the puzzle pieces?
>> It'll be, the three of us
will get the puzzle.
>> PROBST: So the three
gatherers for Casaya will be
Shane, Aras, and Danielle.
That means Bruce and Cirie will
solve the puzzle.
La Mina, who is going to gather
puzzle pieces for you guys?
>> Terry, Austin, and Nick.
>> PROBST: Terry, Austin, Nick.
That means Dan and Sally will
solve the puzzle.
All right, take your spots.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
For reward and immunity,
survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, Shane!
>> PROBST: Shane and Terry out
first.
And a collision right off the
bat.
>> Come on, Shane!
>> PROBST: Shane and Terry
untying quickly.
>> That's it, Terry, way to go,
buddy!
>> PROBST: The faster you get
those pieces back, the more time
you give your tribe to solve it.
>> Attaboy, Shane!
>> Come on, Shaney.
>> PROBST: Terry is through his
knot.
He got his piece lowered.
He's got it unhooked and he's
heading back.
Shane losing a little time.
Shane using his teeth.
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: Puzzle pieces are
heavy.
Go!
Austin on the course for La
Mina now.
>> Get after it, Austin!
Get after it, bro!
>> You got it, Shane.
>> PROBST: Shane has his rope
undone.
Shane unhooks and Shane is
heading back with a piece now.
Austin untying quickly.
>> Good job, Shane.
Nice job, Shane!
>> PROBST: You gotta drop it.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Aras on the course
for Casaya, trying to make up
some time.
Austin has his knots
undone with his second puzzle
piece; Aras working the knots
for Casaya.
Austin back with the second
puzzle piece.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Nick now heading out
for La Mina.
>> Go, Nick!
>> PROBST: La Mina leads, two,
one.
Aras still working on the knots
for Casaya.
Nick working on the knots.
Aras has his undone.
Aras heading back now with the
second puzzle piece for Casaya.
Casaya still trying to make up
some time.
Nick's still working on the
knots.
Aras back with the second puzzle
piece.
Go.
Danielle on the course for
Casaya.
Nick has the third puzzle piece
for La Mina.
>> Go, Nick! Go, Nick! Go!
>> PROBST: Danielle using her
teeth on those knots, trying to
make up some time for Casaya.
Nick coming back with the third
puzzle piece.
One piece left for La Mina.
Terry, back out on the course.
Danielle giving it everything
she has.
Not making up much time.
Terry now working on his knots
for the final piece for La Mina.
Danielle has the third piece for
Casaya.
Terry working on that last
piece.
Puzzle pieces are heavy.
Danielle, trying to handle it.
Terry has his rope undone.
>> That's it, TD!
>> PROBST: Terry coming back
with the fourth piece for
La Mina.
Danielle back with the
third puzzle piece.
One piece left for Casaya.
La Mina with the lead.
>> Come on, Shane!
>> Once we get the first one in,
we got it.
>> PROBST: Terry's back with
the last puzzle piece.
Start solving it.
Dan and Sally quickly getting
to work.
>> Roll it.
Come on, now fix it, fix it.
>> That doesn't work.
Let's use the other one.
>> Rotate that one a little bit.
>> No.
>> PROBST: Shane got to get back
quickly with that last puzzle
piece.
Trying to make up a lot of time.
>> Try this side.
>> PROBST: Dan and Sally
struggle with that first puzzle
piece.
>> Shane's got it! Awesome!
>> PROBST: Shane heading back
with the last puzzle piece for
Casaya.
>> Face up.
>> PROBST: Go! Bruce and Cirie
starting to solve their puzzle.
>> I'll hold it.
>> Okay.
>> Like this or like that?
>> PROBST: Dan and Sally have
had a bit of a head start but
making no progress.
Both tribes looking for some
sort of pattern, something
they can lock into.
>> Hey, there's two cheekbones
right here.
>> PROBST: Bruce and Cirie,
working together.
Think they're onto something.
>> That's it. That's it.
>> Let's move this side over.
>> We got one. We got one.
>> PROBST: Casaya thinks they
have their first piece.
>> They got a piece.
>> Lift this up. Lift this up.
>> PROBST: Casaya thinks they've
figured out a pattern.
>> Hey, Sally, look.
>> PROBST: Dan spying on Casaya
for help.
Casaya with a second piece.
La Mina trying to catch up
simply by copying.
Still got to figure out how to
get the piece in.
>> This one.
>> Spin yours a little bit,
Bruce.
>> PROBST: Casaya working on
their third piece.
Casaya has their third piece.
La Mina falling farther and
farther behind.
A lot a stake-- a big reward
feast, immunity, power over
who goes to Exile Island.
Casaya right on the edge of the
last piece, if they can get it
to fit.
La Mina still working.
>> Step on it. Step on it.
>> PROBST: Casaya wins reward
and immunity!
(Casaya tribe cheering)
>> You did it, Bruce!
>> PROBST: Casaya, huge win.
>> Bruce, you hold that,
brother.
>> Good job, Bruce.
>> PROBST: Immunity keeps you
safe from Tribal Council
tonight, and you have a big
decision to make.
You're going to send one person
to Exile Island right now; that
person cannot be voted out
tonight.
(Casaya tribe whispering)
Casaya, who's it gonna be?
>> Sally.
>> PROBST: Sally, going to Exile
Island.
Boat's waiting.
>> See you guys. Good job.
>> PROBST: Keep in mind, Sally
will get another clue to the
whereabouts of the hidden
immunity idol.
Whether or not somebody's
already found it, who knows?
La Mina, all I have for you is a
date tonight with me at Tribal
Council.
Somebody going home.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
See you at Tribal.
Casaya, it's time to party.
Have a good time.
Boat's waiting for you.
>> Exile Island, for me, is my
saving grace.
In every other case, the
negative downside has been to be
away from the tribe.
In this case, me being here
today is a good thing, because I
felt like there was a pretty
strong alliance between the four
guys and that I would be the one
to go.
So it put things in a really
different perspective.
Today, it's actually saving me.
>> "Clue number six: It is not
found here, but it is in the
shade for most of the day."
It's so important that I'm here
right now and that I have this
opportunity.
Assuming I don't get dumped on
for the next couple of days,
this is a gift to be here,
so I'm thrilled.
It's like a little vacation,
some girl time, get away from
all those boys for a while.
It's exciting and frustrating to
think that there's an immunity
idol out here somewhere,
but it's overwhelming.
You really don't know where to
start.
I'm safe tonight and I'm going
to wake up tomorrow safe.
I'm just privileged and giddy to
still be here, so...
Even it's on Exile Island by
myself.
(children laughing, shrieking)
>> We had won the reward
challenge.
La Mina is demoralized.
We knew they were going to
Tribal Council tonight.
We're in the middle of this
Panamanian fishing village.
We knew we were going to eat.
I'm just so, so happy to be here
right now.
>> I'm coming, I'm coming.
>> I was so joyous to see
all those little kids come
running up to the boat, and
they just grab your hand, and
they have these big smiles on
their faces.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> It was so cool.
A young boy grabbed my hand and
asked me if I wanted to eat,
and I was like, "Yes, I want to
eat."
>> Oh! Oh, God, it is so
good.
>> Oh, my God.
>> This is the first thing other
than water I've had in 16 days.
>> Oh, my God.
Sure more food.
They just kept handing you, you
know, rice and soup, and then
some cheese with chicken and
then barbecue chicken.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I'm so happy right now.
>> I just kept eating and eating
and eating 'cause I...
just went crazy and just at
everything in sight.
Oh, it was amazing.
>> I'm ecstatic.
It was just really nice to be
around people, other than these
people.
You know, and to see kids, that
made my day.
Just to see those kids-- oh!
Those kids remind me of my
family.
I saw this one little girl, she
looks exactly like my niece.
Oh, God, I miss my kids so bad.
I can't even think about it
right now.
It was nice.
It was really good.
Much needed.
I know it's only day 15, but
damn, we really needed that.
>> Yay!
>> I saw one of the villagers
smoking, and I was like, oh, no.
The next thought was "All right,
I can give him my shoes and I
can give him my shorts and I can
give him my shirt and I can give
him my buff...
And here's the deal-- if the guy
would've been like, I want your
underwear too, I probably
would've been naked for the rest
of the afternoon for just one
cigarette.
>> Shane, I'm not happy with
that, buddy.
>> This is probably a really bad
decision.
I remember sitting there in a
stupor going, "Oh, my God, I
can't believe a cigarette is
affecting me like this."
It just shows me how devastating
nicotine is to the body, on
every level.
>> You're enjoying that way
too much.
Amigos, amigas.
No Espanol, but this... so much.
>> The reward kind of brought us
together, but that's the thing,
it's like a double-edge sword
for me.
Yes, yay, we won.
I won food, but now that gives
Shane time to kind of backtrack.
>> I'm really gonna puke.
>> I should never have treated
you like that.
I apologize, okay?
>> I accept.
>> When we leave here, and my
life is normal, I promise you
that I'm going to be a different
person.
And I don't owe anybody on this
island anything except you.
>> Courtney and Danielle,
they're easily persuaded by
Shane's nonsense.
You know what I mean? Damn!
In a way, I almost wanted to
lose, because I really felt that
Shane was going, and then
hopefully, it was Bruce.
(karate yell)
(applause)
But now that we won and
everybody's all in love again, I
don't know.
Damn!
(drums playing)
(villagers speaking Spanish)
(child squealing)
(man singing)
>> I'm so happy right now.
>> You know, today's experience
was one of the top five
experiences of my life.
I was touched and overwhelmed in
so many different ways.
Right when the darkness is
coming, there's this beautiful
dawn, and there's this beautiful
bonding experience.
We got to feast.
We got to hang out.
All the stuff that had gone on
the night before got... sort of
got washed away with the
victory.
It was a really, really great
day.
(birds singing)
>> You know what the saddest
part is?
We knew where the first piece
went.
We had it figured out.
We knew right where it went.
We went in, and we laid it down
there, and it wouldn't fit.
>> That was the key to the whole
puzzle.
>> Losing the immunity challenge
was bad.
It was... it was game seven for
us, and we lost it.
Now Sally's got immunity from
Tribal Council tonight, and, uh,
we've got to vote off one of
our guys.
>> How can we lose a challenge
with a puzzle when we have a
NASA engineer on our team?
I mean, how do you do that?
>> I don't know.
>> This is a young people's
game right now.
You know, we can take you a lot
further in this...
>> Right.
>> ...than he can.
>> If Sally was here, obviously,
we'd take her, but, you know,
physically, he's the weakest.
>> The four of us are all very
close and have an incredibly
strong bond, and I know that
this has to be incredibly
difficult on Terry to even
consider eliminating Dan, but
somebody has to go home, and I
don't want it to be me.
>> I had it.
Sitting in that very spot was
the answer.
You know, the center piece can't
rotate now.
It cannot fit, and to...
I'll never know why...
>> Well, no use pondering
it anymore.
>> It's true.
It's going to be...
We're going to have to sort that
out, 'cause two v. two gets kind
of sketchy.
>> Do you think Austin is
interested in leaving?
>> I don't think so, but I...
I can ask him, but I-I really
doubt it.
>> I ain't going against Terry.
>> Yeah, I can't vote against
Austin.
>> I don't know what's going to
happen tonight.
It's probably going to be two v.
two.
Uh, Terry and I versus Nick and
Austin.
>> I was talking to Dan.
He's pretty convinced it's going
to be a two v. two tonight.
>> Yeah.
I-I-I...
He's-He's a friend of mine.
I like him.
We have crap loads in common
with all the flying and
everything like that, but I feel
like I'm putting on my Joe Torre
hat and making a decision for
the strength of the team, and...
>> Yeah.
>> ...there's a couple of
challenges where he's... not
come through.
>> Yeah.
>> It could have been us, but it
wasn't.
It was...
It was him, so...
>> Yeah.
>> I should probably talk to
him.
I think that the remaining three
strongest men would be me, Nick
and Austin.
Dan's odd man out.
And I feel bad, but
that's-that's the way it is.
>> My whole job is about having
a game plan in place, and if
it's not quite working out,
stepping back, and I didn't do
that.
Instead, I picked up the puzzle
piece and started looking
around randomly.
And you know what?
If I did that in space, you die.
>> You know, we-we made a pact
not to lie to one another and
tell each other the truth and
stuff.
>> Right. Absolutely.
>> And, uh, you know what?
If...
I'd take you to the final two
with you and me if I could,
so, um...
I-I feel like I'm making the
decision for the strength of
the team tonight.
>> I hate leaving.
I hate leaving.
>> I definitely... I wanted to
talk to you first.
I didn't want to make it a
surprise.
>> Hey, you know, my fault.
My bad.
I got to take responsibility for
that.
And as much as I, you know,
would, you know, love to stay--
I want to be here-- hey, you
screw up, you got to... you
know, you got to take the hit.
>> Dan and I have something even
more in common than anybody
else-- soaring to all kinds of
heights above the Earth-- and
having to vote him off is a
highly emotional decision,
because he's something else.
Dan has the right stuff.
>> PROBST: Welcome back to
Tribal Council.
Let's start by talking about who
is not here.
Austin, how big a part of this
tribe is Sally?
>> She's a huge part, but you
know, we had the boys' club and
Sally, um, but she was saved by
the move that, um, Casaya made
today.
>> PROBST: So, Nick, it was
going to be Sally, the next
out?
>> Yeah, Sally would have been
next.
>> PROBST: Terry, do you think
Casaya knew that?
Sensed that?
>> It was immediately known that
they were going to pick Sally.
That meant that we four guys had
to vote one of us out.
So, a maybe stronger player is
now going to be leaving the
game, versus having Sally in
there, so it was a smart
strategic move by their point,
big time.
>> PROBST: Nick, how tight is
this group?
Because it's about to be
splintered.
>> The group's amazingly tight.
I mean, we were able to talk
openly tonight.
It's not a surprise to who's
going to be leaving tonight.
It's understood that, you know,
when you're part of a team, you
might be the weaker physical,
you might be the weaker mental--
whatever your role is-- and we
accept that.
So it's-it's been a very
businesslike process tonight.
>> PROBST: Well, I'm looking at
the four of you, and so far,
nobody's face is giving anything
away.
I don't know if it's you,
Austin, Terry or Dan.
>> It's me.
Uh, they were very up-front with
me to tell me that, uh, it's my
turn tonight to go, and today,
three people performed their
job, and two people didn't.
And one of those two people is
immune, and the other one is
sitting right here.
And I'm willing to take
responsibility.
At the same time, I'd be lying
if I didn't say I was kind of
hoping, uh, that it was going to
go maybe a two v. two.
>> PROBST: Meaning a tie
between...
>> A tie, you know, and Terry
and I go one way, and, uh, Nick
and Austin go the other way.
>> PROBST: Terry, there's an
obvious two versus two scenario.
Did that go through your head
at any point?
>> Strategically, we weren't
going to have to do this till
we got to the final four, and
now we're the final four of this
tribe, and what I'm doing is,
uh, making a managerial
decision.
>> PROBST: Austin, was it clear
in your mind that there was one
person who just needed to go?
They're holding us back.
>> I would never use those words
to say about my buddy Dan Berry.
There's nothing about him that
needs to go.
We are just down to a situation
where somebody has to go.
Dan was the weakest of the four
of us.
>> PROBST: Dan, what will this
tribe be losing if you go home
tonight?
>> I do a lot around the camp.
I built the fire shelter.
I built the, uh, fireplace.
Uh, Dan Fuego-- I-I take care of
that part.
Um, I'm pretty good in the
water, and in general, I'm a
great puzzle solver.
I don't know what happened
today.
But they are losing a
substantial contributor.
>> PROBST: So, Dan, are you just
taking the sword on this one?
>> No, I'm not.
Absolutely not.
If it was my choice, this would
go two v. two, and we'd have
a little challenge going on
here.
I expected to last a lot longer
than this.
And in fact, yesterday, I
thought I was lasting a lot
longer.
You know, I'm-I'm solid with
five people.
I know there's one person in
front of me, for sure, if we
were to lose again.
It's just... it's incredible how
fast things turn.
>> PROBST: Okay, so it does seem
like tonight's vote is a bit of
a foregone conclusion, but I've
seen weirder things happen.
Well, Terry, you have been to
Exile Island.
The immunity idol could come
into play.
You'll let me know after the
vote if that is indeed the case.
It is time to vote.
Nick, you're up.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Dan.
Austin.
Dan.
That's two votes Dan, one vote
Austin, one vote left.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island, Dan.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good luck, my boys.
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: Dan, the tribe has
spoken.
Time to go.
>> See you, Dan-o.
>> See you, Dan.
>> PROBST: Seemed like a tough
vote.
Probably won't be your last.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
New blood changes everything.
>> There they are.
>> Hey, come here quickly.
>> We're home, baby.
I'm ready to get in there, see
if I can come out victorious.
>> You come over, and we will go
to the final five.
>> PROBST: Terry wheels and
deals.
>> I'm just looking for two
people to swing the total game
our way.
>> PROBST: And Bruce gets
whacked.
>> You know what?
>> I just hit Bruce in the face
with a machete.
I'm out of here.
>> I was a little surprised by
Terry's decision.
I would never have voted for
Terry, but he's got to play his
game.
I know that you did what you
felt you had to do.
I respect that, and I wish them
all the best.
This was a wonderful adventure.
I loved every day out here, and
the only thing I really have to
say is, thank you to my family
for letting Dad go off on
another crazy adventure.