>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Terry felt the pressure to
crash the Casaya bonds.
>> It's really imperative to try
to make some allies before the
next immunity challenge.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
You've got to follow that rope!
...the tribe was divided into
two teams of three.
Terry, Danielle, Courtney win
reward.
The reward was a barbecue
feast...
Ready.
...and the chance to play in
a second surprise challenge...
Aim.
...for a brand-new car.
Fire.
>> Yes, yes, yes!
>> PROBST: Terry wins the GMC
Yukon.
>> Unbelievable.
>> PROBST: The feast winners
arrived in style and fired up
the grill.
>> Cheers.
>> PROBST: Then Terry made a
bid for a three-way alliance.
>> I would do anything to get
us to a final three.
>> I'm 100% behind you.
>> PROBST: Back at camp...
>> We're going to vote off
Danielle.
>> Right, but then there's still
Courtney.
It'll be me, you and Courtney.
Right.
>> PROBST: Shane's plan made
Cirie suspicious.
>> If he could take Courtney to
the final two, he just may win
a million dollars.
So Courtney, to me, is more
dangerous now than having Terry
around.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
>> Hold on, Court, he's failing,
I can see it.
>> PROBST: Once again, Terry was
unbeatable.
(Courtney grunts)
Terry wins his fourth straight
immunity.
Back at camp...
>> If you want to be here
tomorrow, me, you and Aras
have to vote Courtney.
>> PROBST: Cirie enlisted Aras
and Danielle into her plan to
get rid of Courtney.
>> Shane wants to take Courtney
to the final two.
I think Terry wants to take
Courtney to the final two.
Some kind of way, Courtney's
going, believe that.
(Courtney whistling)
>> PROBST: Courtney and Terry
thought the plan was to get rid
of Aras.
>> We're going to send Aras
home, so I'm feeling pretty
damn good.
>> PROBST: And Shane was sure
Danielle was the next to go.
>> That's it, Danielle, one,
two, three, four, then we each
move on one more spot.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council...
The 11th person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island...
Shane, Terry, and Courtney
were shocked at the results.
Courtney, the tribe has spoken.
Five are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> At Tribal Council, I thought
we were all going to vote
Danielle out, and without me
knowing, Cirie, Danielle and
Aras voted Courtney out, so I
was shocked.
>> Coming back from Tribal was
a little bit uncomfortable
because Shane wanted to go to
the final two with Courtney.
So to reassure Shane, Aras and
I came up with the story that
we couldn't tell him we decided
to vote Courtney because we
didn't have time, we were
leaving for Tribal and he was
up in no-man's-land.
>> Right.
>> I think it would have been
easiest to take Courtney to the
two, but Cirie assured me that
our alliance is still good.
So there's five of us left now,
Danielle goes next, and then
we're in the final four.
Man, it's nice to not have that
moron here running her mouth.
>> Don't sugarcoat it, how do
you really feel?
>> I'm just so happy that
chick's gone.
>> Last night was the fifth
failure for me in trying to get
numbers on my side.
Danielle and myself, we were
going to take Courtney to the
final three.
We shook hands on it, we looked
each other in the eye, and I
was lied to.
So as far as I'm concerned, if
Danielle's the next on the
chopping block, that's fine with
me.
Not my problem anymore.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, we have taken
elements from past challenges,
put them together to create a
four-stage obstacle course.
Here's how it works:
On my go, five of you will dig
in a circle of sand looking for
a bag.
First four to find the bag, move
on to the second round.
For the second round, carrying
that bag, you will race to
untie a wooden snake.
The first three to get to the
finish with the bag and the
snake move on to the third
round.
For the third round, you're now
carrying the bag and the snake
as you race over a sand hill,
into a water pit where you will
untie a large fish.
The first two to get to the
finish with the fish, the bag,
and the snake, move on to the
final round.
For the last round, you'll
square off head-to-head as you
are now carrying all three
items you've collected through
a series of wooden tunnels and
towers.
First person to the finish wins
reward.
Want to now what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Today you're playing
for love.
Face-to-face in person with
your loved ones.
>> Oh, man.
>> The winner of today's
challenge is responsible for
allocating who gets love and
how much love they get.
We'll draw for spots and we'll
get started.
First four to get a bag and
cross the finish move on.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Shane digging fast, Terry
digging quickly.
Aras right the middle of it
digging down.
Four people going to get a bag
and move on to the next round.
Danielle has her hands on her
bag.
Danielle moving on.
Terry moving on.
Two more spots left.
Cirie, Shane, Aras looking for
love.
Who's going to get it?
Aras going to get the third
spot.
One spot left.
Cirie still in it.
Shane still in it.
Keep digging.
Cirie has her hands on the bag.
Cirie moving on.
Shane, first one out.
It's Aras, Cirie, Danielle and
Terry.
Three people moving on to the
next round.
Survivors, ready?
Go.
First three to get a snake
untied and get to the finish
with both of their items move
on.
Terry and Aras quickly at work
on their snakes.
Danielle untying a snake.
Cirie in it now, she's untying
a snake.
How quickly can you get the
knots undone.
Danielle with her snake undone.
She's first down.
Danielle has her bag, heading
for the finish.
Aras has his snake.
He's heading for the finish.
Terry has his snake.
Danielle moving on, Aras moving
on.
Terry gets the third spot.
Cirie out of the challenge.
Here we go.
It's Terry, Danielle and Aras.
The first two to get to the
finish with the bag, the snake,
and the fish move on to the
final round.
Survivors, ready?
Go.
Terry lost his snake, got to go
back.
Aras with a bit of a lead.
Terry trying to make up some
ground.
Everybody at the fish at the
same time.
>> Come on, Aras!
>> PROBST: Aras first undone
with his fish.
It's down to Terry and Danielle.
Danielle using her teeth.
Terry has his fish.
Holding on to it with his teeth.
Danielle got to hurry up.
Aras moving on, Terry moving
on, Danielle out of the
competition.
Here we go.
A showdown between Aras and
Terry.
Who's going to be in charge of
allocating the love?
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Terry lost his fish, he's got
to go back.
Aras with a bit of a lead right
off the bat.
Aras up the first tower, Terry
right behind making up some
time.
Aras almost loses his bag.
We're dead even.
Terry and Aras coming to a
meeting point, who's going to
get there first?
They're stuck.
They're fighting for it.
Nobody wants to give up an inch.
Terry's going to get through
first.
Terry almost loses the fish.
Terry and Aras are neck
and neck again.
Aras loses his bag and has to
go back and get it.
Terry down through the tower.
Aras out of it.
>> Where's the love, baby?
>> PROBST: Terry wins reward.
>> PROBST: Okay, now we get to
the fun part.
First, we're going to bring out
your loved ones.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Terry, here's your
wife, Trish.
>> God.
>> That's so awesome.
(applause)
>> I love you.
>> Love you.
>> PROBST: How's he look?
>> Good.
>> PROBST: Aras, here's your
mom, Theresa.
(applause)
>> Hey, Mom.
>> You rock!
You rock, baby!
>> PROBST: Danielle, here's your
mom, Denise.
>> Mommy.
(applause)
(crying)
Mom, don't cry.
I love you.
>> PROBST: Cirie, here's your
husband, H.B.
>> H.B.
Yeah, H.B.!
>> Yeah, baby!
>> Hey, bunny!
(laughter)
I miss you so much, baby.
>> I love you, too, honey.
>> I'm so proud of you.
>> PROBST: Finally, Shane,
here's your son, Boston.
(cheers and applause)
>> Oh!
Oh, Boston!
>> Oh, man, all right!
>> I love you so much.
>> I love you, too.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Terry, here's how it's going to
work.
Two of the loved ones are going
to go with their survivors on
an overnight stay.
You'll go to a beautiful villa,
you'll have pizza, lots of
stuff to drink, plenty of
snacks.
In addition, you'll have
separate bedrooms, so you'll
have a little privacy.
That's for two of the loved
ones.
One loved one is going to go
back to camp with their
survivor.
You get to live as they've been
living for the last 31 days.
That leaves us with two people.
This is where it gets tough.
One of the final two will get a
hug with their loved one and
that is it.
And the last person will get
nothing more than this,
separated by 20 feet, and that
person will be sent to Exile
Island.
So the first decision I need is
who is the first loved one that
is going to join their survivor
on the overnight stay.
>> Myself and Trish.
>> PROBST: Trish, come on over,
give your man a hug.
Okay.
Next decision, who's the second
loved one that is going to join
you on the overnight stay?
>> Boston, Shane.
>> Oh, God, God...
Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Now, the next
decision, which loved one gets
the experience of going back to
camp?
>> H.B., you're up, hubby.
>> Oh!
Hi, baby.
>> PROBST: All right, Terry,
toughest decision now.
Two people left.
Both their loved ones are here.
Who's getting the hug?
>> I'm going to send Aras back
to camp tonight.
>> Oh.
>> So Aras gets the hug.
>> Aras, come meet your mom.
Get some love.
>> I'm so proud of you.
>> When I get home...
>> Yeah?
>> Will you please on the table
have, like, five dinners?
>> Everything.
I'll just make everything you
want.
Oh, my God.
>> I love you.
>> PROBST: Danielle, Denise, I'm
sorry that this is as good as it
gets.
Hopefully, it was enough,
Danielle, for you to be able to
see your mom.
>> I love you so much.
And we all love you so much, the
whole family and Pugsy.
We miss you so much.
>> Give everybody a big kiss
for me when you get home.
>> I'm so proud of you.
>> Mom, you're making me cry.
Stop.
>> Be strong.
>> I will.
She's so cute.
I love her.
>> PROBST: All right, Danielle,
Exile Island awaits.
The boat will pick you up.
Okay, Aras, Cirie, H.B., Shane,
Boston, Trish, Terry, head on
out.
>> I was so disappointed to have
my mother, like, five feet in
front of me and not be able to
talk to her and give her a hug,
and everybody else did.
That really sucked.
Maybe this is Terry's head
right now.
It's all good.
He'll get his.
Terry, he's out for me.
He's pissed off because I
basically ruined his strategy
plan to take Courtney to the
final two.
And you know what?
I don't care.
I was really pissed that I
couldn't see my mom, but at the
same time I'm not going to sit
and cry about it.
And how do you like that?
I don't have to share this with
anybody.
This is fabulous.
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> Were they good?
>> Mm-hmm, when we was hungry
it was.
>> Yeah?
>> Why are you bringing the
stuff in here?
This is where we sleep at.
>> Oh, yeah?
>> Coming back to camp with H.B.
was kind of funny for me
because I knew he didn't know
what to expect.
>> Yeah.
But that's okay.
>> How's it feel to see her,
man?
This is our reality.
>> I think it was shock for
H.B. to see how primitive we
live.
>> What is that?
>> Oh, these is snail butts.
>> Oh, snail who?
>> Butts.
>> Butts?
>> Like the guts or something.
I use it to attract the fish.
>> Oh, okay, good.
>> It's called chum in the
water.
>> Oh, okay. Hmm.
>> So, like, you see a fire like
that, that means there's tons of
embers.
You kind of try to make a
teepee.
You want to have a lot of air
under the sticks.
>> Okay.
(laughter)
Man down! Man down!
>> We never made fire.
We ain't never been camping.
H.B. is just like me.
He's never been anywhere.
He's a couch potato.
>> What you going to do with
that, drink it?
>> Yeah, that's how we do it.
>> That's water.
(laughs)
>> Oh...
With the dirt and stuff in it?
>> It's good for you.
(laughs)
>> Okay.
I thought that was, like, a
basin that y'all wash y'all
feet in or something.
Wow.
(laughter)
>> Seeing H.B. here, green, not
really knowing anything, it
helped me a little bit to
appreciate how far I've come.
It almost makes me feel like I
kind of underestimated myself
for 35 years.
And now it's like, "Damn, you
can do anything!"
>> Oh!
>> Three types of ice cream.
>> Dude, eggs!
>> Vanilla, chocolate, and
strawberry.
>> And milk, pancake mix.
(gasping)
>> What is this?
>> Is that a cerveza?
>> We went to this beautiful
house here in Panama.
In the kitchen, just sitting
there were four different kinds
of pizza.
Two bottles of white wine, two
bottles of champagne, a 12-pack
of beer.
>> Oh, my God!
Beer!
(gasping)
I just want to eat it raw.
There had to have been about
three pounds of bacon.
All kinds of snacks.
Pretty much as much as you
wanted.
It was all there.
>> Look at this!
>> This is how I was in 1978.
>> I was really surprised at
the condition that Terry was in.
I almost gasped.
I've never seen him so
emaciated and so worn out.
Oh, I can't wait to get that
beard off him, and get him back
to his hot-looking studly self.
>> Day one, each tribe is on
its own island, okay?
>> Oh, that's cool.
>> We get there, and, dude, I'm
freaking out.
If I could have chosen one
reward and lost the rest of
them, I've got my son on an
overnight with all the food I
could ever want.
By day six, I'm out of my mind.
I'm ready to quit.
I don't because I think about
you, and I think about how you
would have killed me if I would
have quit.
You know, my son would have
missed out on this amazing
experience and I'm so grateful
I didn't quit.
>> This is what Exile Island is
all about and the hidden
immunity idol.
It's a shrunken head.
I'll try to unflatten it a
little bit.
>> That's a good thing to have.
>> It is a very good thing to
have.
We started talking about the
game and the fact that my wife
is such a perceptive person and
great at strategizing.
Immediately she just invested
her whole mind into what I was
going through and interjected
herself into the game.
>> I'm starting to feel like
it's going to end up being all
men at the end.
>> We're going to take out Aras.
Me and Cirie, when it gets to
the four probably.
>> But Danielle is gone.
>> She knows she's done.
>> I tell you what, if I were
her...
>> I'd look for the idol.
>> But the idol is in his bag
that's in your bedroom right
now.
>> He hasn't told me, I'm
serious.
>> You know, the thing that was
really weird is that Terry's
wife, Tricia, is more
competitive than Terry.
So she was the one that wanted
to talk about strategy.
What a lovely woman, but
unbelievably competitive.
It's been hard out here without
you.
>> I think my dad's doing
really well in the game 'cause
he knows how to play the game.
He's really smart and athletic.
He's like a brother to me more
than a father.
We do everything together.
And he's like a kid and he,
like, he does fun things with me
and stuff, so I really missed
him.
>> I love you.
>> I love you, too, Dad.
You okay?
>> I'm so good.
I just remember him saying, you
know what I mean, like, "Shane,
here comes your son, Boston."
I just couldn't believe it.
>> This is nice.
>> I didn't really give a crap
that much about the bed.
It was who I was sleeping with
was extremely wonderful.
(both laughing)
We had some private time, but I
tell you, just the snuggling,
just the snuggling and being
able to sleep with my wife was
just a warm, warm feeling.
God, this is awesome.
>> Okay, baby.
>> Do you see that stuff right
there?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Those branches?
>> Yeah.
>> Can you get that?
>> Yep.
As soon as I got up, it was
like, "Okay, we need to do the
fire, okay, we need to get food,
okay, we need to get water," and
I'm like, "Oh, my God, we just
woke up already!"
>> We need to reserve our
energy, so he needs to help us
and he needs to see what we do
daily.
But he likes it.
He doesn't mind.
Thank you, honey.
>> Uh-huh.
Cirie and Aras have been working
me like a dog and it's bugging
me a little bit.
It's like, "Honey Bunny, can you
go get us some water?
Honey Bunny, can you get us some
more twigs?
Honey Bunny, can you cut this
coconut?
"Honey Bunny, can you scale this
fish?"
I'm like, "Oh, gosh, you're
killing me out here."
Y'all got your own little
servant, boy, I tell you.
(Cirie laughing)
Mm-mm-mm! Y'all are livin' it
up, living it up!
But I know that I'm not going to
be here long, so I'm going to
help as much as I can.
Boy, here goes nothing.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> I'm so proud of Cirie.
I mean, words can't even
express, you know...
(sobbing): ...words can't even
express how I feel just to know
that Cirie is doing this for her
family.
It's wonderful to see that she
would come out here and take
this risk for us.
I love you so much, baby.
>> I love you, too, honey.
>> She's my hero.
>> Bye, honey.
>> All right, baby.
>> See you, H.B.!
>> Take care of him, honey.
>> Having H.B. at camp brought
back why I'm here.
I'm not just here for me.
I'm here for us as a family.
I want H.B. to have a better
life.
I want us to have, like, a
wonderful life.
>> What up?
How was it, guys?
Did you get your good night's
sleep in?
>> Oh...!
>> You are so welcome.
You know what?
The choices were so clear to me.
>> When Terry and Shane returned
from their reward, Terry was
kind of explaining his reasoning
for delegating the time the way
he did.
>> Terry, just to let you know,
24 or not 24, man, everybody out
here wanted to see their family
members.
Just as bad as you wanted to see
Trish, I wanted to spend the
night with my mom, and to, like,
think, "Well, it's just a mom,"
that rubs me the wrong way when
you say that.
>> When you get married, in my
viewpoint, there's no choice.
If I had a choice to see my wife
or I had a choice to see my
mother, I'm seeing my wife.
>> You won your reward.
Congratulations, you got to be
with your wife.
I didn't get to be with my mom,
so have a little bit of sympathy
and understanding.
Dude, 33 days, man.
You know?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And that is my rock.
Everyone's got their rock...
>> Right.
>> ...and what you're saying is
"Well, that rock is more
important than that rock."
My mom is huge for me.
>> Here I have some 24-year-old
kid lecturing me-- "My mom is my
rock and she means as much to me
as your wife means to you."
I like the fact that Aras came
unglued.
It showed a part of him that I
hadn't seen and maybe a little
crack that I can take advantage
of.
When you have a wife, you'll
know this.
When it happens for you, it will
happen.
>> The least that I would expect
from a 46-year-old man who talks
about his age over a 24-year-old
all the time is respect.
That doesn't register with
Terry.
But what he's doing is he's
feeding my fire, and the more he
does it, the more I want to beat
him.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Danielle from
Exile Island.
>> Hey.
>> PROBST: How was it?
>> It was awesome.
The weather was beautiful, so it
made my experience a lot more
enjoyable than the first time.
>> PROBST: All right.
Ready to get to today's immunity
challenge?
>> Yep.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Terry.
After four straight individual
immunity wins by Terry, the
immunity necklace is back up for
grabs.
Today's immunity challenge is
going to require balance and a
steady hand.
You are each going to stand on a
very small perch at the top of a
20-foot pole in the water.
On my go, you will lower a
bucket into the water, take that
water, and pour it into a very
narrow bamboo shoot.
As the bamboo shoot fills up
with water, it will raise a
flag.
When the flag is high enough for
you to reach, grab it.
First person to raise their flag
over their head wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot in the final
four.
That is a one-in-four shot for
the million bucks.
One big rule: your feet are on
the perch.
Your butt, your knees cannot
touch the perch.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Losers-- Tribal
Council tonight, somebody going
home.
We'll draw for positions and get
started.
(Cirie shrieks)
For immunity and a guaranteed
spot in the final four.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Terry quickly up with a bucket
of water and he's pouring.
Cirie really taking her time.
Aras pouring.
Danielle pouring.
Nobody hitting the bamboo shoot
yet.
Your goal is to get water in
that bamboo shoot as quickly as
you can.
As the bamboo shoot fills up,
the flag will raise.
Terry's flag starting to raise.
Danielle's starting to raise a
little bit.
Patience and balance-- the key.
Aras gets a little bit of water
in that shoot.
Terry's flag moving up quickly.
Danielle's moving up.
Cirie surprising herself 20 feet
up in the air.
Shane still with nothing.
Aras now on the board, his flag
starting to rise.
Cirie's flag starting to rise.
Shane not having much luck yet,
water going everywhere.
It's pretty even right now--
Terry, Danielle, neck and neck.
Cirie right in it.
Shane has absolutely nothing
happening.
>> 'Cause I've been pouring into
the wrong hole like a moron.
>> PROBST: Shane just now
figuring out the challenge.
>> That's never good, is it now,
Jeff?
That's never good!
>> PROBST: Aras gets a nice bit
of water in that chute, his flag
raises quite a bit.
Immunity on the line.
Terry still with a bit of a lead
over Cirie, Danielle, and Aras.
Everybody in this except Shane,
who's starting to figure it out
now.
Aras catching up, his flag
raises quite a bit.
Terry getting closer with each
bucket.
Aras and Danielle right behind
him.
Terry getting much closer to
where he can reach down and grab
it.
Aras getting close enough that
he can reach down and grab it.
Is it close enough for Terry?
No, not close enough for Aras
either.
One or two more buckets could do
it.
Terry right on the money,
raising his flag quite a bit.
Aras fighting back, not giving
up.
Aras getting closer.
Terry's almost there.
Terry reaching for the flag.
Terry...
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: ...wins immunity for
the fifth straight time!
(Terry yells)
>> Shut up.
(Terry laughs)
>> PROBST: Oh.
Terry, come on over.
You are undefeated in individual
immunity challenges.
Once again, Terry is safe at
Tribal Council.
Cirie, Shane, Danielle, Aras,
for one of you, the game will
come to an end tonight.
Swim on in, I'll see you at
Tribal.
>> (mimicking Probst): For one
of you, the game will end
tonight.
(sings dramatic fanfare)
>> Hoo-ee!
>> That was fun.
Winning the immunity challenge
today was huge because it
doesn't just win me the four, it
vaults me into the final three.
I have the hidden immunity idol,
I don't even have to show up for
the next immunity challenge.
What a relief.
I've had the hugest target on my
back, now the pressure is off.
>> I think she's depressed
'cause she knows she's next.
The plan is for me, Aras, and
Cirie to take out Danielle
tonight.
And I'm in a great space.
I've set myself up so that I'm
safe and I feel like things are
going to be solid.
>> After what happened at
Tribal Council the other night,
Danielle, you know, she blew me
off so I wouldn't feel too bad
sending her off.
And from what I know, she's
going anyway.
>> My guess is it's going to go
down that way, yes.
>> I would love to take Shane
to the final two.
Not that he doesn't work, but
my case speaks for itself.
Going out fishing for people
and cleaning up the camp and
collecting firewood and
building fires and teaching
people stuff.
With a huge target on my back
and winning the challenges,
that I think would be a
no-brainer even for a heavily
loyal Casaya jury.
>> Shane thinks I'm going home.
It's so funny how he thinks he
knows what's going on and, like,
he's controlling everything.
He doesn't know anything.
>> I was in an alliance with
Shane, but I found out he
wanted to take Courtney to the
final two and so that pretty
much puts me off the hook.
I no longer feel any obligation.
>> Yeah?
>> ...and she's good.
>> I've done a really good job
of setting Shane up for a
situation like this.
Shane thinks I'm his puppy dog.
He thinks he can tell me to do
this and I'll do it because, up
until this point, I have.
Which really makes it easy
for me to do things pretty
inconspicuously.
>> I know that Shane is looking
to get rid of me, I'm looking
to get rid of him.
Terry's out for me, he's pissed
off, but I have a strong bond
with Aras and Cirie.
Cirie especially.
I just trust Cirie with my life.
Like, I really, really do.
It's so key in this game to have
one person at least that you can
trust.
So I'm pretty confident right
now with my alliance.
>> This one is going to go
Danielle.
>> Right.
>> And then the next one we'll
go Aras.
But we can't look like we're
betraying Aras, because then
he'll remember that on the jury.
>> Right.
>> And you're straight, you feel
good, and you're 100% with me?
>> 100%.
No problem.
>> You, Danielle and Aras
aren't ... me, correct?
>> No. No, no, no, no, no.
>> All right.
I feel good.
I think we're probably pretty
good to the three.
>> Yes.
Shane thinks that me, him and
Aras are going to vote for
Danielle when, in all actuality,
Aras and Danielle are going to
vote for Shane.
Aras and Danielle-- those are
the two people I've had the
longest alliance with.
At the same time, this is still
a game and you have to look at
it logically, because I think
Danielle will be able to beat
me in the final two.
Courtney didn't hold true to
Danielle's friendship, and I
think Bruce kind of had a love
affair with Danielle, and I
don't know if her and Austin
bonded at Exile Island when
they almost died.
So Danielle is a threat.
>> I think I've set myself up so
that I'm safe, and I feel like,
at this point, I could beat
anybody.
I feel like I could.
I mean, I feel comfortable, as
comfortable as you can feel out
here.
(laughter)
Like, am I going tonight?
Just let me know if I'm going
tonight.
>> I love Aras, but I'm going
to do everything, everything
that I can do to get myself
further in the game.
So it is safe to say that
somebody's going to be
surprised tonight.
There's going to be huge
fireworks, bigger than the
Fourth of July.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Austin...
Sally...
Bruce...
and Courtney...
voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
Terry, let's talk about the
loved one challenge.
Was that a tough dilemma being
in charge of allocating the
love?
>> It's always a tough charge
when you're put in almost a
"God" position.
But the initial thing for me,
obviously, was my wife, followed
by Shane and then H.B. got to
go see what Cirie was up to.
Uh, you know, I'm afraid if I
offended anybody, but I think it
all worked out okay.
>> PROBST: Cirie, how did your
husband like living at camp?
>> He was thankful for the
experience, um...
but ready to go home.
You know, he's like a city guy.
But for him to get to see what
we go through, it left him
extremely, extremely proud.
He said I was his hero.
Um, this is something once-in-a-
lifetime for us.
>> PROBST: Shane, you waited a
long time for Boston to get
here.
>> It was, um...
Yesterday was unbelievable.
It was a magical, magical, like,
vacation with him and we were
just hanging and being dad and
son, and as I watched the sun
go down, I just thought to
myself there's absolutely
nowhere else on the planet
Earth I would rather be.
>> PROBST: Let's get to the
immunity challenge.
Terry wins again.
Five straight.
Aras, there's an obvious
competition between you two.
>> For me, it just becomes more
fun in a competitive sense.
You can look at it any way you
want, every time is a crack at
him.
The thing of it is with Terry is
that he knows it just takes
one crack and he's done.
>> PROBST: At what point do you
stop saying "Just one crack and
he's done" and start saying
"Terry's looking pretty good
right now."
>> Well, Jeff, this way that I
look at it, is the challenges--
just one part of the game.
You can win all the challenges
you want.
If you don't win people over,
you don't win the million
dollars.
>> PROBST: Shane, can you be
trusted at this point in the
game?
>> Yes, absolutely.
I have not lied to anyone.
I have not cheated anyone.
My integrity is 100% intact.
>> PROBST: How about you,
Danielle?
Can you be trusted?
>> Um, when you feel like you
lose trust with someone or
someone's doing something
sneaky behind your back or
talking about voting you off
first, then you make a move.
That's how I look at it.
You have to make moves in the
game to further yourself.
I mean, that's the whole point
of the game, isn't it?
>> PROBST: I'm looking at the
immunity challenge today and
here's what I saw.
Cirie, Danielle working hard.
Terry, Aras working hard.
Shane pouring the water down
the wrong hole, kind of making
jokes.
If you were less comfortable at
this point in the game, would
today's immunity challenge have
had a different feeling for you?
>> You know, I have one thing
in my favor which is, I feel
like I'm sort of being carried
to the end because I don't
know, I feel like everyone here
thinks they can beat me if we
get to the jury, or maybe more
easily than, like, Cirie who's
a mother of three and an
unbelievable person, or Aras
who's the golden boy who at any
point could levitate home, you
know what I mean?
There might be a little more
rust on me, you know?
>> PROBST: Danielle, how
worried are you, being two days
away, that you have no idea
what's in store tonight?
>> I'm scared.
I mean, I've been away for two
days on Exile Island.
You don't know what's going on,
you come back to camp and, you
know, there could be other
alliances formed or whatever.
I can only wish and pray.
I... I don't feel comfortable.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
the vote.
Terry has the individual
immunity necklace.
You going to keep it?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: And once again this
hidden immunity idol has yet to
have come into play.
If somebody has it and they're
going to use it, they'll use it
after the vote.
It is time to vote.
Aras, you're up.
>> (whispers): Shane, sorry,
brother.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Danielle.
Shane.
One vote Danielle, one vote
Two votes Shane.
12th person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island...
Shane.
(Shane chuckling)
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: That's enough votes.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Oh, my God, I'm going to
have a chocolate ice-cream bar
in about one minute... I mean
one minute.
>> PROBST: Shane, the tribe has
spoken.
>> PROBST: Well, the last two
Tribal Councils, the person
voted out has been absolutely
shocked, so if trust wasn't an
issue, it certainly will be
from here on out.
Six days left, grab your
torches, head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> What are you talking about?
>> PROBST: Cirie stands up to
Terry.
>> Make an attempt to talk to
people like you want to be
talked to.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: The Terry-Aras
rivalry gets personal.
Two battering rams!
And Danielle makes a move.
>> I will swear on it now.
>> We are going to go to the
finals, you and I.
>> It's the right time to align
myself with Terry.
>> Ah... I got duped.
I was blindsided.
I really thought that me, Aras,
and Cirie were, uh, locked in.
This will be the toughest thing
I ever do in the history of my
life.
I just want to tell you, Bobo, I
love you so much, I'm sorry I
didn't win, I tried my hardest,
and Daddy's proud of himself,
although disappointed, and I
love you.