>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
At Casaya...
...Shane wanted out of his
alliance.
>> But I can't do that unless
you guys allow me to take my
son's name back.
>> PROBST: The next morning...
>> I want to ask you guys if I
can take my son's name...
>> Done.
>> Done?
>> PROBST: ...the Casaya women
granted Shane his wish, and the
alliance of Shane, Courtney,
Danielle, and Aras was broken.
>> Well, if that's how you feel
about it, then fine.
Get out of the alliance, you're
off anyway.
See you later, bye.
>> PROBST: At La Mina, alone
amongst four men, Sally knew she
was in trouble.
>> The four guys are kind of
doing, like, a boys' club thing,
but I think it's shortsighted.
>> PROBST: The challenge was
both for immunity and reward.
You will go to a local
Panamanian fishing village,
you'll have a Panamanian
barbecue.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: But in a twist, one
person from the losing tribe
would be saved.
The person you send to Exile
Island will not go to Tribal
Council tonight.
That means they cannot be voted
out.
Terry's back with the last
puzzle piece.
La Mina took an early lead.
Dan and Sally quickly getting to
work.
>> Roll it.
>> PROBST: But when Dan and
Sally faltered on the puzzle,
Casaya...
>> Step on it! Step on it!
>> PROBST: ...put together the
pieces to victory.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Casaya wins reward
and immunity!
Casaya, who's it going to be?
>> Sally.
>> PROBST: Casaya sent Sally to
Exile Island, saving her from
certain elimination.
Boat's waiting.
>> I felt like there was a
pretty strong alliance between
the four guys and that I would
be the one to go, so tonight
this is the safest place for me
to be.
>> I'm so happy right now.
>> PROBST: At the Panamanian
village reward, Casaya filled
their bellies...
>> Oh, my God.
I just ate everything in sight.
>> Hyah!
>> PROBST: ...and got their
minds off the game for an
afternoon.
>> I know it's only day 15, but
damn, we really needed that.
>> PROBST: While Sally searched
for the idol that Terry had
already found, back at La
Mina...
>> It's been a couple challenges
where he's not come through.
>> PROBST: ...the boys' club was
about to lose a member.
>> I think that the remaining
three strongest men would be me,
Nick, and Austin.
Dan's odd man out.
I feel bad, but that's the way
it is.
>> PROBST: At a painful Tribal
Council...
>> There is nothing about Dan
that needs to go.
We're just down to a situation
where somebody has to go.
>> PROBST: Sixth person voted
out of Survivor: Exile Island...
Dan the astronaut calmly
accepted his fate...
Dan, the tribe has spoken.
...and his tribe stood
respectfully as he gave his
final salute.
Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(theme song playing)
>> I'm freezing.
>> Courtney, I'm not-- I'm not
the only one using it.
It's also Cirie-- it's under
Cirie as well.
>> And, like, no warmth.
I was shaking.
Last night was the worst night I
ever had.
I literally did not know what to
do with myself.
Everyone was cuddled and dry,
and I'm wet and, like, alone in,
like, a little ball.
I mean, I'm... and also I just
feel like my innards, like,
inside is, like, freezing still.
Everything I own is soaked.
And Shane just, like-- instead
of, like, even feeling that I'm,
like, shivering and, like-- he
just was elbowing me with his
elbow.
It was just like, "Ugh."
I cannot trust Shane and I don't
want to deal with him anymore.
He had a freak-out on us, and he
said, "Please give me back my
son's name.
I want out of this alliance."
So, we're like, "Oh, good-bye.
Fine, we'll see you later."
>> I know I'm still an outsider
to Casaya.
I just want to make the merge.
The whole ball game's going to
change big time and I'm gonna be
there standing.
>> Exile Island for me is my
saving grace.
It's not hurting me one bit to
be out here away from the rest
of my tribe.
Happy to still be here and
excited to see what's in store.
I've been spending some time
just digging a little here and
there, and I don't know if Terry
has found the immunity idol.
I hope he hasn't.
Maybe I'll get lucky.
>> We'll have slugs for lunch
and beans for dinner.
>> Sounds good to me.
I'm very anxious about what's
going to happen next.
Depending on when the merge
comes is going to play a huge
role in how far Terry, Nick,
myself, and Sally will be able
to make it in this game.
>> "What the heck is it?
This thing we are looking for.
Could it be buried treasure?
"Or something worth much more?
I'd start searching
On your back beach.
"Look for something
That ain't quite right.
But when you finally find it,
"You may be more comfortable
Tonight."
>> We just got some tree mail
telling us we were going on a
treasure hunt.
Marvin Gaye said it best:
"Let's get it on" up in this
piece.
>> I'm hoping it's something
edible.
edible, too.
I mean, what else could we have
to make our thing more
comfortable other than a
Posturepedic bed?
>> We got tree mail saying
there'd be something on our back
beach that wasn't quite right.
On the way out there, we're
thinking, "Oh, I hope it's
something to eat.
"I hope it's really something
substantial to eat."
>> Whoa, firewood.
>> Got wood, that's nice.
"Do not open any of the packages
until you arrive and are
gathered together with the
members of the Casaya tribe."
Uh-oh.
>> Merger, boys.
Pack it up.
Whoo-hoo!
I couldn't be happier.
That means we're going to be
reunited with the other tribe
tonight, ready for a new
adventure, ready to shake things
up, get to know some new people.
That's what this is all about,
so... can't wait.
>> All right, I'm gonna start
feeding it over to you guys.
We're down six-four.
The merge could be disastrous
for us.
If we don't get somebody to
switch over right away, we'll
just get picked off.
We need to get over there and
find out who exactly is aligned
and who is not.
I'm gonna hit up Bruce and see
where he lies, Shane as well.
What I'm hoping for is to switch
the numbers to our advantage,
and then we just pick them off.
My ace in the hole is the
immunity idol.
I would personally not want to
pull it out of my pocket till
the final four, but if I need to
use that thing strategically,
then I'll do it.
>> It'll be sad just to leave
the tight dynamic that we have
here with the four remaining
members, but I'm ready to meet
some new personalities, get in
there, start bobbing and weaving
like Sugar Ray Leonard, see if I
can come out victorious.
>> We're not doing anything.
I don't think any of us feel
like doing anything today.
You know, we're just collecting
wood, making fire, eating rice,
drinking water.
Really exciting, isn't it?
Riveting. Oh!
>> Delicious.
>> ♪ And nutritious. ♪
>> Who is it though?
>> It's three of them.
>> So who went home-- Austin...
or Terry?
>> We're having a nice lazy day.
We had a feeling a merge might
come and we saw the boat coming.
Is that Nick in the back?
>> No, that's Terry in the back.
>> We knew they were hungry and
all of us just chowed the rice,
'cause... 'cause we're heathens
and we didn't want to share.
>> I hope they feel strong and
feel like building us a new
shelter.
>> Hey, come here quickly, come
here.
All six of us right here, right
now.
>> We're eating as much rice as
we can and then we bring it in
together while they're paddling
like, "Stay together, don't give
them a thing."
>> I'm so proud of us.
We've worked ourselves here.
They have less than us.
We have more.
We stay together, we get to the
top six.
>> One, two, three...
>> ALL: Believe!
>> Damn!
>> We're going to welcome them
in with open arms.
"Welcome to our house, but we're
going to vote you off one by one
by one by one."
>> You've arrived!
>> Come on in!
Finally! Whoo!
>> Terry and Austin and I are
paddling into shore and they're
standing there waiting for us
with open arms.
They just welcomed us into their
home.
>> Welcome back.
You look great.
>> How are you?
I'm Shane.
>> Introductions start.
Everybody says hello, the hugs
come.
>> I guess my initial concern is
Bruce.
Bruce does have a relationship
with Terry, per the original
tribes.
This is Survivor.
You know people can flip-flop.
>> Hey, my man.
>> Oh, God, I've lost you!
>> Good to be here, Bruce.
Good to be here.
I'm so excited to have your face
around with this merge, meet the
new people,
I could just feel a sense of
wonderful things about them.
>> I'm so happy to be here, man.
>> Hey, Cirie!
>> Hi to you, too.
>> Terry and I respect each
other, and just to be with him
again is, like, just a pleasure.
>> Sally!
>> Sally made it, too.
(cheering)
>> Sally!
>> I get here to this new place
I've never seen before and
I'm just, like, "What is going
on?
"Everybody's together.
Is this the merge?"
And Bruce comes, like, trucking
out of, like, the group of
people, and is the first person
so excited to see me and gives
me a huge hug.
>> Yeah!
>> And then there was this
crate.
>> Let's open it up!
>> Let's open it.
>> Another message, oh, no.
>> Read it, Bruce.
>> "Congratulations, you're all
one tribe.
"Here are your new tribe buffs
and tribe flag and paints.
"Give yourselves a name and
design and paint your new tribe
"flag.
You'll find drinks, snacks and
supplies..."
(all cheering)
>> Oh, fruit!
Oh, Bruce.
>> Sally, pub snacks, honey.
Pub snacks.
>> Chocolate!
>> Inside the box was fresh
fruit and jarred, pickled
goodies, crackers and cheese
and wine.
I kind of wanted to slap myself
for eating all that rice before
they got here.
>> I am a glutton right now and
it feels spectacular.
>> It was a very cordial
gathering, everyone sharing
everything, everyone being
really pleasant, and I could
sense there probably was a
little bit of sizing up.
I was a little surprised at how
well we were welcomed.
I thought there might be a
little bit more of a competitive
edge, but I didn't see it.
>> Oh, good, this is really big.
Spread that far corner.
>> Yeah.
>> You can attach here and here
and here and to another post,
so...
>> La Mina came over from the
merge with the tarp and our
shelter was really great, but I
think this one that they're
building now is gonna be
amazing.
>> And this side over here, you
might be able to keep this side
attached to that tree open.
>> All right, here's the deal.
It's hard to tell, but I think
Terry does not have the
immunity idol, so the next time
he doesn't get immunity, he's
out.
>> It's a whole new ball game
and I'm all about getting it
swung to my side, and so we're
just looking for two people.
Two people to swing the total
game our way.
And one to definitely make a
good swing vote, but two to
clinch it.
So if you were worried at all
about what may happen in the
next vote...
All we need is one person, and
we'll be even.
And I'll tell you this, listen.
You come over, and we, we will
go to the final five.
We thought Bruce might be a
little bit of an outsider here,
so I instantly attempted to
bring him into the La Mina fold
and give him sanctuary right
away.
I will look you in the eye and
shake your hand on it.
And you know, you know...
>> And I know you're the man to
do it.
>> That's right.
>> You know I am, too.
>> If anyone would flop, I
think it would be Bruce.
I think Bruce is the most
worried about being accepted,
and I think he might have some
issues with, you know, wanting
to be accepted by Terry.
Aras's and my strategy with
Bruce is to make him feel like
our leader so that he won't go
away, he won't fall on us.
>> Bruce, you're... man, you're
doing-- now, it's intensive,
man.
You run the show now, man.
Hey, no, come here.
Hey. Hey, Bruce.
I know that, and I'm saying,
right now, here, hey, you run
the show.
>> Yeah.
>> You let them know.
>> You're the senior member of
the tribe, buddy.
>> I'm the swing vote for both
sides.
It's such a wonderful feeling to
be in this power position
because I know I'm gonna go a
lot further guaranteed.
I've thought out the best
options of all the other nine
players, and they know it.
As much as I respect all of
them, this is a game now.
Outwit, outlast, outplay
everybody.
(thunder crashes)
>> Come on, fire.
>> Bruce and...
>> Terry?
>> And Terry.
I know. Damn.
>> You know what...?
>> Oh! Oh!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
>> What happened?
>> You okay, Bruce?
>> You all right?
>> I cut my tooth.
>> Oh.
>> We're building the shelter,
Bruce needed some rope cut, and
I have the machete.
It goes through the rope and
hits him in the face, the sharp
end.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry, Bruce.
Neither of us were really
thinking, I guess.
>> You chipped, you just chipped
the top.
The second tooth, the incisor.
>> And that chipped a bit of his
tooth and cut his lip.
It was just a sickening sound.
Initially, I'm, like, "I'm
gone.
"I just hit Bruce in the face
with a machete.
I'm out of here."
>> You all right?
>> He's going to need to get a
stitch.
>> I got a machete in my mouth.
>> You know what?
He may be on the DL for one day
and that's it.
He'll be back.
>> I am, I am not leaving this
game, let me tell you.
>> Let's see.
>> It did leave him a big gash
in his face.
I mean, I panicked at first.
I'm, like, panicking about
numbers for a second for sure.
>> You know what?
You're out of the game for a
day, you'll be right back.
All right, right back.
>> Stitch me, I'm cool.
I'll be here.
I ain't leaving.
I ain't leaving you guys.
I got too much to do with you
guys.
Nick felt so bad.
I mean, I just saw it in his
face.
He was in shock.
He could have killed me, he
could have sliced my face open.
>> You all right, buddy?
>> I had a tooth come through my
lip before, no biggie.
>> You are a tough son of a gun,
man.
(laughs)
>> Psychologically, I want to
outwork them, I want to
outperform them, and when it
comes to competition, I want to
beat them all.
>> Our tribe name is Gitanos,
which means "Gypsy" in Spanish,
I believe.
And since I'm an art teacher for
34 years, I was designated to be
the artist to create the flag.
And it took me a while to think
of what kind of lettering I want
to do, how to lay it out, what
will stand out the best.
I mean, I want our group to be
proud of this banner, and I want
to do a great job for the group.
Yeah, no question, yeah.
>> Straight up and down.
>> I went off with Aras to
collect some firewood.
I made some ambiguous chat about
what's been going on at camp,
because he and I did have a
pretty good bond those days at
Young Guy Beach.
>> Um, I mean I'm good with
everybody.
There's no one I don't get along
with.
>> The only thing that I learned
was it was gonna be a lot harder
than I'd hoped to flip anybody
over.
>> Okay, Shane...
>> Cirie?
>> Yeah, you and Cirie.
It would be you, Cirie and us
four, and then you wouldn't have
to worry about anything for the
next two weeks.
Think that would be cool?
>> We can definitely try.
Terry approached me and said,
"Here, you and Cirie, let's go
right now, the six of us."
You know, I mean obviously it's
desperation, but I mean, "Why
would we want to join your
tribe, homie?
"We're gonna ride this out and
vote you off one at a time.
There's no reason to flop."
He's grasping at straws and I
get it.
I would be doing the same thing.
>> I talked to Shane already,
and our group of four would like
to offer you and Shane the
opportunity to take the burden
of Tribal Council off your
shoulders for the next two
weeks.
>> Terry tells me that, um, I
mean, it was almost laughable.
It was like he's offering me
something.
I don't think he's in the
position to offer me anything.
>> Okay.
>> And if we can solidify this
thing, that's even more time of
worry-free life around here for
the next couple of weeks.
>> Right. All right.
Well, I'll get back to you.
>> All right.
>> It was like a dictionary
salesman.
I mean, I already have an
encyclopedia collection here,
and you want to sell me a
dictionary?
>> Am I in?
I don't even know what you're
talking about.
>> I know there is.
>> You want to live the next two
weeks burden-free?
>> If you take a look at where
we're at, we're in a really
good spot if we just stay where
we are, you know?
Maybe somebody will flop.
It's not going to be me.
And I know it's not going to be
her.
I mean, getting to the merge
with the numbers is the biggest
part of the game.
And I just know for me, I'm
not flopping, so...
Yeah.
>> We were trying to sway Shane
this morning, and that's not
going to happen, not at all.
In fact, he doesn't even want
to talk about it.
We're not sure about Cirie, and
we're not sure about Bruce.
So, even if we get one person,
and it's five on five, it could
be time to pull out the
immunity idol that they don't
know about.
So, it could be my ace in the
hole for the rest of the game.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, so tell me about the
merge.
Nick, how did it go?
>> The merge was great.
We were ecstatic over at La
Mina to get the news.
It's been two days of love.
The game was set aside for a
day or so to get to know these
people, and it's been amazing.
>> PROBST: You guys ready for
today's challenge?
>> ALL: Yeah!
>> PROBST: First things first.
Take back the immunity idol.
Thank you, Austin.
Tribal immunity is no more.
This is what you covet now.
Individual immunity from here
on out.
If you have this immunity
necklace around your neck,
you're safe at Tribal Council.
If you don't, as you know, you
could be going home.
Very clear.
Okay, let's get to today's
immunity challenge.
It is a very simple test of
endurance.
You are going to hang upside
down with your arms and your
legs wrapped around a pole.
You're going to hang there for
as long as you can.
You fall off the pole, you're
out of the challenge.
Last person left hanging wins
immunity, is safe at tonight's
Tribal Council.
The other nine, somebody will
be going home.
Anything not clear?
>> Pretty clear, Jeff.
>> PROBST: We've randomly drawn
for spots.
Take your spot, we'll get
started.
All right, everybody climb up
your ladders.
All right, get on.
First individual immunity
challenge is officially on.
Hanging from arms and legs.
Don't drop headfirst if you
drop.
What's hurting already, Cirie?
>> My arms... are hurting.
>> PROBST: Those arms are going
to give, Cirie.
Make sure you let your legs
down.
Cirie first out.
Take a spot on the mat.
Very good chance that somebody
hanging up there needs immunity
and doesn't know it.
Been at it ten minutes.
And you start to feel your
muscles cramp.
Courtney doing some acrobatics,
dangling from her legs.
Sally not moving.
Terry not moving.
Shane struggling to get a
different grip.
Austin struggling to hang in
there.
Aras drops out, joins Cirie on
the mat.
Eight people left hanging.
Who wants immunity?
Who feels comfortable going to
Tribal Council without it?
Bruce not worried.
>> Ahh!
>> PROBST: Sally down.
Sally joins Bruce, Aras, Cirie
on the mat.
>> Let's get some food, Jeff,
and I'll get down.
Get my a cheeseburger, Jeff,
I'm out of here.
>> PROBST: There ain't no food.
>> No food?
>> PROBST: No temptations.
Shane drops out.
Danielle is out.
Courtney drops out with a smile
on her face.
Three people left hanging.
Been up there 20 minutes.
Austin, Terry, Nick, fighting
for immunity.
Austin relaxes, gets another
bit of energy.
>> Terry, get off.
I'm struggling, man.
>> No way, Hoss, hang in there.
>> PROBST: Now the negotiations
begin.
>> Come on, buddy, I know you
got pride, but let's save our
energy.
>> PROBST: Austin trying to
convince Terry to get down so he
has a shot at immunity.
So, Terry, you're in a bit of a
situation.
>> Yeah, they're my buds.
>> PROBST: But this is a game.
Voluntarily giving up immunity
is about the riskiest thing you
can do.
30 minutes.
This challenge is full on into
the willpower stage.
Mind over matter.
How badly do you want it?
Austin's out.
We are down to two, Terry and
Nick, fighting for immunity.
Been up there 40 minutes now.
Both guys trying to stretch it
out.
Where you feeling it, Terry?
>> My right shoulder.
>> PROBST: Where are you
feeling it, Nick?
>> Forearms.
I just need to get some blood to
them.
>> PROBST: Nick drops out.
Terry wins the first individual
immunity.
Terry, come on over.
Turn around.
Congratulations.
You're safe at tonight's Tribal
Council.
Everybody else is fair game.
Grab your stuff.
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> Possessing both the immunity
necklace and the immunity idol,
uh, it's a godsend.
The immunity idol will be going
with me to Tribal Council
tonight.
Hopefully I won't have to use
it, unless I want to use it as
a bribe down the road.
I was thinking about you and
your karate, and your, you
know, your level of mastership.
You are one of my things taking
me away.
>> La Mina's tribe, I have a
bond with them, especially with
Terry, 'cause I was first with
La Mina.
Terry, to me, is the number one
head stand-up guy of everybody
here.
I'm kind of right in the center
of both tribes.
They want me to come over
there, and the other tribe
wants me to come over to that
side.
I just.... I'm glad they have a
high respect for me.
>> We've got to get this thing
jumping before we leave for
Tribal.
>> We're going to Tribal
Council tonight, and I'd be
lying if I said I thought there
was anything that could save me.
Want to say a quick prayer with
me, man?
>> Yeah, I would.
>> Because I'm taking off from
this place, I know it...
Lord, I just thank you for
giving me the opportunity to
come out here...
I don't think I could have
beaten Terry in the immunity
challenge, so I went in knowing
that I was going to try to make
myself look weak, so I was
putting on an absolute
Oscar-winning performance.
I was over there falling down
and coming back up.
Thanks for allowing me the
opportunity.
Praise Jesus.
That was my plan was to show
that I wasn't that strong.
But it doesn't matter what
happens, I'm going home.
There's no question about it.
>> Whoever gets voted out
tonight is not part of the jury.
That's why I was holding on for
so long, is one of my goals is
to make the jury.
And now I know that since Terry
has immunity, the next two
walking the plank are Austin and
I.
I really hope that I make it
through this one more vote.
It's a big, big night.
>> Bruce!
Factor!
>> Shane gets on the royal
bellow, blows the horn, or
whatever they do to announce a
Casaya meeting, you know, makes
a big show of it.
It's like kindergarten, you
know.
He has to look after his
children, make sure they're all
on the same page.
>> Of course.
>> What are you talking about?
First of all, this was a very
tough two days.
They were all over us.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm very proud of us for
staying together, so let's, uh,
talk about...
>> Who do you guys want to go
for?
>> Courtney?
>> I'm for Nick.
>> I'm kind of up in the air
still.
>> You're kind of up in the air?
>> I'm up in the air, so...
>> Okay.
>> I'm up in the air.
(Cirie sighs)
>> Um, Nick seems like Terry
number two...
>> Yeah.
>> ...to me, just physically.
Um...
>> I don't know why I feel like
Austin's the call, but you guys
give great points for Nick.
>> You didn't know the...
>> The reason why we would want
to vote out Austin first were
because we thought he was more
of a physical threat than Nick,
but, you know, I think everybody
got all freaked out because Nick
did well in the immunity
challenge today, so then the
bottom line is, I don't care.
I just want one of them gone,
and one of them is going.
One, two, three...
>> ALL: Believe!
>> Couldn't be much more obvious
than that, huh?
>> No.
Would we be that cocky?
>> You know, if-if you're going
to just talk to each other, then
talk to each other, but, like,
all of a sudden parade off...
>> Well, what do we do, man?
>> You can be cocky, but it's
cooler if you're not.
>> Terry's pretty irked about
the way Shane organized the
meeting, so we'll just...
You know, the little shot across
the bow that we can provide,
we'll vote for Shane.
>> No, hey.
Guys, this situation is the
situation.
There's no...
>> I know, I know.
>> There's no like, uh...
>> There's no easy way to do it.
>> ...prettying it up.
>> I know.
>> We just wanted to get
together-- the six of us--
figure out exactly what we're
doing, communicate, and to be
honest, I don't care what they
think.
You know what I mean?
If they have a problem with it,
okay.
I mean, they can have as big a
problem as they want.
They're, they're still going,
one at a time.
Barring any psychotic episodes
from Bruce wanting to be
dramatic and flop.
Who knows what he's capable of?
We just need to get this one
person off.
>> PROBST: Courtney, catch me
up.
What's the new name of the new
tribe?
>> Gitano.
It's Spanish word for gypsies.
>> PROBST: Who came up with
that?
>> It was sort of, like,
collective, and everyone agreed
it would be a fun name, so...
>> PROBST: Terry, when you got
the note at La Mina saying, get
in the boat and head over to
Casaya, was that good news or
bad news?
>> Personally, I was hoping for
one more immunity challenge, and
with that, we hoped to knock
them down one more peg prior to
the merge.
>> PROBST: Nick, how do you
change what appears to be
inevitable?
>> You just stir things up if
you can, best you can.
Basically, try to identify the
fringe players, and then exploit
their position in their tribe,
and, you know, hopefully,
communicate that to them in a
way that they understand, and
they're willing to come over to
your side.
>> PROBST: Bruce, you get
separated from your tribe,
you've been to Exile Island
twice.
I would think your loyalties are
spread all over the map.
You have interactions with all
kinds of people here.
>> It's been a roller-coaster
ride.
I mean, I always seem like I was
always on the outside looking
in, and, uh, whoever I was
teamed up with, I was willing to
just try to do my share, and I
feel they respect me, and I have
a high respect toward all of
them.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about the
immunity challenge today.
Nick, you were fighting to not
give up.
>> I mean, obviously, the main
thing through my mind was, I'm
going to be on the block tonight
without immunity, but the one
chance I had today was to,
hopefully, show them that this
is how bad I want to stick
around, and if, hopefully, my
actions...
Um, hopefully, they...
You know, hopefully, they spoke
for me.
>> PROBST: Austin, you were
hanging in there as long as you
could today.
What was going through your
mind?
>> Well, Jeff, I had a lot
going through my mind.
I was waging an inner struggle,
because I could be on the
chopping block because I was
really strong, so I was fighting
whether I wanted to act like I
couldn't hang... or keep hanging
and try to beat Terry, but long
story short, I opted to come
down, and, uh, probably going to
pay the price for that.
>> PROBST: You say, "Opted to
come down."
The strategy was, appear weak?
>> Something along those lines.
>> PROBST: Shane, the second you
guys found out there was going
to be no food to tempt you down,
it was plop, plop, plop,
everybody dropping.
That's the only reason you were
staying up there at all.
>> I mean, me personally?
Yeah, I mean, I was waiting for
a cigarette or a donut or
a coffee or something, and when
you weren't going to come with
any of that, I was down.
You know, we're sort of sitting
in this position where we hold
the cards for right now, so of
course, I jumped down.
I'm going to conserve my energy.
We have our numbers, and we're
going to stick true to them.
>> PROBST: Aras, a little
worried that this is a very
cocky group of six right now?
>> I'm not worried about our
confidence in the six.
The whole thing of it is, is the
wrench is, is the immunity idol.
There... It's still an immunity
idol that could very well be in
the hands of people who just
came to our beach.
And so that is probably the only
thing that I'm worried about.
>> PROBST: Would you be knocked
over if somebody flipped from
your side tonight?
>> I'd be stunned.
>> PROBST: So, Courtney, you're
pretty confident.
>> Uh, I would be very shocked,
yes.
>> PROBST: How about you, Cirie?
>> Yeah, I would be, uh,
flabbergasted.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Okay, Terry has the
immunity necklace.
I doubt he's giving that up.
In addition, several of you have
been to Exile Island.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol, and you want to
use it, you'll let me know after
the vote.
It is time to vote.
Nick, you're up.
>> Cool guy, man.
Just voting for you 'cause you
led the charge to get me out of
here.
>> This makes me really sad.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Shane.
Shane.
Two votes Shane.
Three votes Shane.
Shane, that's four votes Shane.
Nick.
Four votes Shane, one vote Nick.
Two votes Nick.
Nick.
That's four votes Shane, three
votes Nick.
Nick.
We're tied.
Shane with four votes, Nick
with four votes.
Nick.
That's five votes Nick, four
votes Shane, one vote left.
The seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island-- Nick.
Nick, you have not been to
Exile Island, so unless somebody
has given you the immunity idol,
you need to bring me your torch.
Nick, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> (whispers): Cirie.
>> (whispers): Nick.
>> PROBST: Well, as day 18 comes
to a close, you are the final
nine.
Seven of you will ultimately
comprise our jury.
Two of you will make it to the
end, one will win.
With 21 days left, a lot of game
left to be played.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
>> I have it.
>> Shut up.
>> No.
I have it.
>> PROBST: The hidden immunity
idol begins to work its magic.
>> Even if he does have it,
which he doesn't, he's not about
to give it away.
>> You're calling me stupid?
>> The hidden immunity idol has
really shaken things up.
It could change the game like
that.
>> I'll give you the immunity
idol.
>> All you kids in your mid-20s
that are in my situation,
confused, not sure which
direction life's pulling you,
you're just trying to find
yourself-- I urge us all,
please, be hungry, be foolish,
block out the noise, find
yourselves, be who you
potentially are, and be true to
your dreams and what you really
want to do.
If we all maximize that personal
freedom, and we'll change the
world.