>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> We've come a long way, baby.
>> PROBST: Terry was the lone
wolf from La Mina.
>> I've got a huge target on
my back, but the longer I hang
out, the longer I get to see
how they end up turning on one
another.
>> PROBST: The reward challenge
revealed what the tribe really
thought of Courtney.
Who is the most annoying person
out here?
Everybody says Courtney.
>> God!
>> PROBST: Cirie answered the
most questions correctly.
Cirie wins this challenge.
Who are you sending to Exile
Island?
>> Terry.
>> PROBST: Terry.
And she chose Danielle and Aras
to go with her on a spa reward.
Back at camp...
>> I'm going to have to live
with this for the rest of my
life.
>> PROBST: ...Courtney was
pained by the revelations from
the challenge.
>> I was so happy to be here,
like, yesterday.
I don't want to be here.
>> PROBST: Bruce's pain was
physical.
>> My whole back, my stomach,
the pain is just increasing.
>> PROBST: At the reward, Cirie,
Aras and Danielle enjoyed
themselves.
>> If I'm out of the game
because of this, at least I got
to do this before I went.
>> PROBST: While back at camp...
>> Oh, God!
>> PROBST: ...Bruce's health
took a turn for the worse.
>> Are you allergic to anything?
>> PROBST: The medical team
arrived to assess him.
>> He can't stay here.
>> PROBST: And Bruce was
evacuated.
>> See you in a minute, Brucey.
>> PROBST: Alone in camp,
Courtney and Shane made a pact.
>> If I need your vote, would
you trust me and not break my
back?
>> You know I want to be on
your backside, and I would like
you to be on mine.
>> Okay.
She is a dream to take to the
final two.
Anyone could win against her.
Anyone.
>> PROBST: When Cirie, Aras
and Danielle return...
>> Welcome home.
>> PROBST: ...they learn the
news about Bruce.
>> We lost a member.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Bruce went home?
>> Yeah. He was med-evac'd out
of here.
And I have no idea if he's in
the game, if he's okay.
I don't know anything.
>> Wow.
>> Is that Terry?
Wow.
>> PROBST: Terry was picked up
from Exile Island...
>> Welcome, Jeff.
>> PROBST: ...and landed at the
camp beach.
Bruce is going to be okay, but
he is no longer in the running
for a million dollars.
We're hoping that Bruce will be
back and continue on as a member
of the jury.
It is now down to you six.
Nobody will be voted out
tonight.
Six are left.
Who will be the next to go?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
>> What are you thinking of
using for bait?
>> I got hermit crabs.
I want to see...
We're running out of food, so
we got to use every method to
catch.
>> Bruce being gone out of this
game was a good thing for me
because I got to skip a
challenge.
And pretty much every immunity
challenge coming down the road
I've got to take.
It is really imperative to try
to make some allies and,
hopefully, tie up one or two
members before the next
immunity challenge.
>> I was going to the rocks
today, and I saw this thing,
just like that, and it was
just...
I was, like, wow, BlackBerry.
It reminded me of my BlackBerry.
So I grabbed it, and I've just
been playing with it.
It's got texting, e-mail, phone,
Web browser.
It's got everything.
When I think about something I
want to tell my partner, I
shoot him off, or talk about my
son, because my son can text on
his cell phone.
It's actually helped my day.
I'm communicating with people
not on this island.
>> Shane found a piece of wood,
and is actually calling it his
BlackBerry.
>> Look for the address.
>> And he sits down and he,
like, pretends like he's
communicating with people.
>> Send.
>> Come on.
>> Check mark.
All good.
>> He's nuts.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: It is for reward.
Here's how it works.
You'll be divided into two
teams of three.
Each of you will be attached to
one long rope which runs the
length of an obstacle course.
On my go, you must follow the
rope while navigating the
various obstacles.
When you reach the final
platform, you'll unclip and,
one at a time, race across a
lily pad run.
You'll then jump into the water
and retrieve a bag.
There are three bags total.
Once you have all three bags,
clip back into the rope and
make your way back across all
the same obstacles to the
finish.
First team to get to the finish
with all three members and all
three bags wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: The winning three
will leave here, fly to your own
private island, where you will
have a barbecue feast.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Steak, sausages, a
cooler of soft drinks and, for
dessert, chocolate cake.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, we'll
randomly draw teams and get
started.
It's Terry, Danielle and
Courtney taking on Cirie, Aras
and Shane.
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
Strategy is going to be key in
this.
>> Help me up.
>> PROBST: Aras helping Cirie
over.
She takes a hard fall right
away.
Courtney, Terry, Danielle
through the hitching post.
Cirie, Aras, Shane right
behind!
Terry, Danielle, Courtney first
to the pole.
Cirie's there.
Somebody's going to have to
help.
Gotta follow that rope!
That's all you gotta do is
follow that rope.
We are still very tight.
Now it's going to get a little
tougher having to crawl under
and over.
Cirie back into the water.
>> All right, back up.
Aras trying to help Cirie.
>> You're going to go
underneath.
>> PROBST: Terry through the
bamboo crawl and on to the
platform.
Danielle's on the platform.
Aras, Shane, Cirie, they have
twisted themselves up.
They have really slowed down,
and they're really in a mess.
Courtney up on to the platform.
Terry unclipped and making his
way across the lily pads.
You gotta jump in and get a bag
out of the box.
Terry up with the first bag!
Aras, Cirie, Shane, you need to
get moving!
You are taking too much time!
Terry back with the first bag.
Danielle making her way easily
across the lily pad.
No trouble.
Shane, Aras, Cirie are all
knotted up, can't figure out
what to do.
Danielle back with the second
bag.
One bag left.
Courtney has no trouble with
the lily pads.
Courtney has the third bag, and
heading back.
Cirie, Aras, Shane are falling
out of this challenge.
Courtney back with the third
bag.
Clip in and head back!
Cirie, Aras, Shane almost look
like they've given up.
Get your asses out of that
water.
Let's go!
Terry, Danielle, Courtney, this
is their challenge to lose now.
Shane finally up on to the
platform.
Shane unclipped.
He's going to give it a go.
Wastes no time!
Hanging on!
Terry, Danielle, Courtney back
at the rope twist with nobody
close.
Shane back with the first bag.
Terry, Danielle, Courtney
through the rope twist.
Home free.
Cirie, Shane, Aras still
fighting.
But it's going to be too little,
too late.
Terry, Danielle and Courtney
with one obstacle left.
Terry across.
Danielle across.
Courtney across!
Terry, Danielle, Courtney win
reward!
Terry, Courtney, Danielle, nice
job.
Barbecue feast is yours.
And a big decision to make.
Cirie, Aras, Shane-- one of
those three is going to Exile
Island; give you a second
to talk about it.
>> What do you want?
>> Whatever you guys want.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Who is it going to
be?
>> Aras.
PROBST: Aras, you know the
drill.
Grab your stuff, boat's coming
in.
>> More beans for us, Cirie.
>> PROBST: Cirie and Shane,
sorry, got nothing for you.
Head on back to camp.
>> Enjoy.
>> We'll see you tonight.
>> PROBST: Terry, Courtney,
Danielle, before we get to your
barbecue feast, you will
compete head to head in another
challenge with an additional
individual reward up for grabs.
Here's how it works: you'll use
a slingshot to fire marbles at
three ceramic tiles.
First person to knock out all
three tiles wins fully loaded,
2007 GMC Yukon.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Sound good?
>> Excellent!
>> PROBST: Take your spots.
We'll get started.
In order for a tile to be
considered hit, it must break
away from two of the four ropes
connecting it.
You can hit the tiles in any
order.
First person to break all three
tiles wins the Yukon.
Ready, pick up your slingshot,
get your marbles.
Here we go, first round.
Ready, aim, fire.
Courtney nicks hers, but not
enough.
Ready, aim, fire.
Danielle breaks her first tile.
Terry clips one, but he's only
broken one rope.
That is not a hit.
Ready, aim, fire.
Terry finishes what he didn't
do the first time, knocks his
first tile down.
Danielle clips a second one,
but not enough.
GMC Yukon on the line.
Ready, aim, fire.
Courtney smashes her first tile.
Terry breaks his second tile.
Danielle just low.
Terry down to one tile left.
Danielle, Courtney both have
two tiles left.
Ready, aim, fire.
Danielle misses left.
Courtney breaks her second tile.
Terry clips his third tile.
That's not enough.
Courtney and Terry both only
have one tile left.
Either one could win this
challenge on this shot.
Ready, aim, fire.
Danielle just misses.
Courtney just misses.
>> Yes, yes, yes!
>> PROBST: Terry gets it!
Terry wins the GMC Yukon.
>> Unbelievable.
>> PROBST: Here's how it's
going to work.
You're going to fly to an
island.
When you land, your car will be
waiting for you.
It will be loaded with
everything you need for your
barbecue.
>> All right, all right.
>> PROBST: You'll return to camp
back later today.
>> Excellent.
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff and
head on out.
>> All right, let's go barbecue!
>> At this point in the game,
from what I understand, the
idol's not here anymore.
It's been found, and now it's
hiding somewhere in Terry's bag.
And so I won't really waste any
of my energy looking for it or
stressing about it because that
part of the game is now out of
my control.
Kind of makes my stay here
pretty unnecessary in terms of
the positives.
>> We were airplaned off to a
far island where we were to
have our feast.
>> Oh, it's gorgeous!
>> Oh, my God!
>> At the end of the runway,
there in front of us was a
brand-new, spankin' Yukon, and
it was righteous, man.
>> Wow!
Oh, mother of...
>> This is gorgeous.
>> The last thing my wife said
going out the door was, "Damn
it, just bring me home a car."
Let's see what this bad boy can
do.
In pile the girls, and off we
drove to this beach feast.
Oh!
>> This is so nice to, like, be
on the winning side of things.
That's like, seriously, like,
was, like, the dream team.
>> Salud!
Congratulations, Terry.
>> Thank you.
>> I would do anything to get
us to a final three.
>> I'm 100% behind you.
I mean, that's a great final
three, wouldn't you say?
>> I'm going to start putting
out some feelers to Courtney
and Danielle today, try to
forge a relationship with those
guys in order to take us to the
final three.
>> The thing is, if you just
win the next immunity challenge
and take Aras out, and the next
one, one of us will win, and we
take Shane out...
>> Shane out.
>> ...and boom, we're final
four, done.
It's been in the back of my
mind to join up with Terry for
like a long time because going
against Terry is one pretty
good shot of actually winning
the million in the final two.
I think that's kind of how
people are looking right now is
who do you want to be up
against in the final two?
>> Well, D, I was talking to
Courtney while you were gone.
You know, we talked kind of
like the dream final three,
final four, whatever.
And if you were with us, and
it was us three and Cirie, you
would have a 75% chance of
winning immunity, and that
would be pitting us three up
against Cirie.
If I can produce the hidden
immunity idol, then, you know,
even so, we've got three people.
We'd have to beat Cirie.
>> Uh-huh.
Terry brought up the fact that
his ideal four would be the
three girls and him, and that's
just a given.
I mean, obviously, he wants
Aras out.
For his sake.
I like that idea, but he's
going to have to change up his
strategy a little bit, too.
I'm not going to make this so
easy for him to win.
>> It's just the two of us, and
we can talk about strategy all
we want.
We're through to the five,
right?
>> Right.
>> If Terry wins immunity, me,
you, and Aras are still
through, because we're going to
vote off Danielle.
>> But then there's still
Courtney.
It will be me, you, and
Right.
Mm-hmm.
If he could take Courtney to
the final two and he may just
win a million dollars.
Against anyone else, I don't
know how good his chances are,
and I think he knows that, so
Courtney to me is more
dangerous now than having Terry
around.
So I just want to get rid of
Courtney as soon as I possibly
can, and then go from there.
Oh, damn, they're getting out
again.
(yelling)
Jump!
>> You do?
>> Yeah.
>> With what?
>> With...
>> A fishing pole?
>> Yeah, where is the hook?
Oh, I see it.
All right.
I'll be back with fish.
(laughing)
I figure how hard can it be?
I've fished before when I was
younger with my dad with a
standard fishing pole.
So I figure, well, everyone
else has tried it.
Let me try it.
Oh, gosh, sorry, snail.
Yuck!
This is so gross!
I need a bigger rock.
(yelling)
Sorry.
Oh! I think I got a fish!
It's going! It's going!
Oh, no!
What's that?
Is that a puffer?
What is that?
Shane is going to be so happy.
I'm scared it's going to come
off!
I can't touch it.
Hold still.
Don't move! Don't move!
Wait till I can get...
Somebody needs to help me.
Dead yet?
Damn!
♪ Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you. ♪
>> Unbelievable.
How did that happen?
>> I was so happy.
I was so, so happy to have
caught a fish, especially a
fish that big, and it's Shane's
birthday.
>> Unbelievable!
>> Happy birthday.
>> I'm so proud of you!
>> To see the look on Shane's
face, it was priceless,
priceless.
>> Cirie Fields caught the
biggest fish out here, the girl
from Jersey.
Captain America has been
swimming around for three
weeks, nothing.
How great is that?
>> Oh, here they come!
>> When we returned from our
reward, we got a pleasant
surprise.
>> I caught a fish, girl!
>> You did?
>> Wow! Awesome, Cirie!
>> You speared it?
>> No, I just fished with the
little thing.
Who would've thunk Cirie could
catch a fish?
That's the joy in waiting for
them to see the fish, for me.
(laughs)
I love it, love it, love it,
love it.
>> Right, right, I agree.
Danielle asked me about, "Well,
if you win, who are you going
to take to the finals?"
You know, "Are you going to take
Courtney?
Because it might be easier for
you to win the million if you
took her."
To be honest with you, if I had
my druthers, I would take
Courtney to the finals, and I'm
sure Danielle would take
Courtney to the finals.
>> I know.
>> I want to make sure that
we're going into this agreement
in a very fair way, so final
three challenge is, top two
finishers go to the finals.
And-and I'm all for that.
You got to beat the best and be
the best.
>> It was extremely insulting
to me when she said, you know,
"I don't want to have someone
being carried in here."
And she didn't even see that,
you know?
I was, like, "Do you underst..."
Like, of course I'm going to
be mad.
Who are you speaking to right
now?
"Someone being carried in."
You're referring to me, because
I'm the easiest one to beat.
>> What is she talking about?
Um... whoever wins what?
I don't know, I've lost that
part.
>> If Terry came in first...
>> Mm-hmm. Whoever came in
second should be the person he'd
take?
>> Yeah.
>> Of course he would tell you
that, because if you look at the
three of us, who do you think is
going to come in second?
Since their little thing
yesterday, Danielle... they done
brainwashed her, and I keep
trying to point out to her, she
wants to go with Terry and
Courtney and myself, which, of
course, I'll be number four.
Come on, now, I'm not stupid.
But why would you want to take
her with us and give her first
or second place?
I keep... I don't know why she
can't see that.
If we take away the person he
wants to take second, he doesn't
have to know who we're gonna
vote.
He can think we're going to
vote Aras.
You can't let him dictate what
y'all should do, and that's
basically what he's doing:
"No, go with me, and then I'll
see who I decide who I want...
I'll take second, maybe the
most athletic, but nine times
out of ten, I'm going to take
Courtney, because I know I can
beat her.
But I'll tell Danielle, yeah,
that's what we'll do,
whoever is number two, then
that's who I'll take."
Yeah, mm-hmm, and I got a
bridge in Brooklyn to sell you.
I want to get rid of Courtney,
like, yesterday.
Some kind of way, Courtney's
going, believe that.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Aras,
returning once again from Exile
Island.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Terry, give it up.
Three individual immunity
challenges, three times Terry's
won.
We'll see if that continues
today.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you are
going to hold your own weight.
Here's how it works.
You are going to each kneel at
the end of a long plank
suspended over a pit of water.
You'll be holding on to two
ropes that are connected to a
hook.
Hanging from the hook is weight.
We'll start with 20% of your
body weight.
Every 15 minutes we'll add more
weight.
As the weight gets heavier, it
will get harder to hold on to
those ropes.
When the weight becomes too
much, the ropes'll slip from
your hands, the platform will
fall, you'll drop into the
water.
The last person left standing
wins immunity, guaranteed a
spot in the final five.
Ready to get at it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, weigh in.
Get started.
All right, everybody has their
ropes.
We're going to release the
weight.
Three, two, one.
This challenge is on.
You are holding 20% of your
body weight right now.
Shane, Cirie, Aras, Terry
all holding right around 34
pounds.
Danielle and Courtney holding
about 24 pounds.
And we're just getting started.
When we reach 15 minutes, we
will add another ten percent of
your body weight, roughly
another 12 to 15 pounds for each
of you.
Shane feeling those ropes
slipping through his hands.
>> I'm not going to make it.
>> PROBST: Shane has lost one
rope.
He's down to one rope.
That rope is not coming back.
Shane now holding all of his
weight with one hand.
Shane lets go.
Shane is the first one out of
the challenge.
Okay, it's been 15 minutes.
We're going to add another ten
percent of your body weight to
the hook.
Three, two, one.
Everybody has another ten
percent now.
(groans)
>> It's burning my hands, the
rope.
>> PROBST: You guys have made
it 30 days.
Nobody give up.
(grunting)
It's slipping.
>> PROBST: Cirie, second one out
of the challenge.
We are down to four.
Aras, Terry, Danielle and
Courtney.
Aras struggling to get a
different grip.
Danielle struggling to hang on.
Danielle, third one out of the
challenge.
We are now down to three.
Aras, Terry, Courtney holding
30% of your body weight.
(groans)
>> Hold on, Aras.
>> PROBST: Aras just lets go.
Two days on Exile Island, too
tough to overcome.
We are down to two: Terry and
Courtney.
>> He's wavering, honey.
You're going to beat him.
>> PROBST: You've reached 30
minutes.
We're going to add ten more
percent of your body weight.
Three, two, one.
Release.
>> PROBST: You are now both
holding 40% of your body weight.
Terry is holding 68 pounds,
Courtney holding 49 pounds.
Terry digging down deep.
Immunity on the line.
>> Watch your weights, Court.
They're getting close to the
bottom.
>> I know. I know.
>> Hold on, Court.
Hang on, honey, he's failing.
I can see it. He's dying.
>> PROBST: The only way to make
sure you do not get voted out
tonight is to win this
challenge.
>> Hold on, Court.
>> PROBST: Courtney down to one
rope.
(groans)
She can't do it.
Courtney's in the water.
Terry wins his fourth straight
immunity.
Terry, come on over.
For the fourth straight time you
win immunity.
You're the only person to wear
this necklace so far in this
game.
Once again, you're safe at
Tribal Council.
For the rest of you, after 30
days, one of you going home
tonight.
See you at Tribal.
Grab your stuff.
Head on back.
>> Oh, I tell you what.
Winning today was awesome.
Somebody from Casaya is going
home tonight, and I think Aras
knows that he's the target, and
he is.
>> Aras is still our biggest
threat.
I mean, no one can beat him in
the final.
>> Right.
>> He's still, like,
competitive, but at least we're
secure for final four.
>> With me, you, Danielle, and
Terry?
>> Yeah, I mean, that's, like,
solid.
So we're gonna agree,
you, me, Danielle and Terry all
vote Aras.
And then Aras and Shane are
gonna vote Danielle out.
And we'll pretend like we're
voting for Danielle.
>> Yeah, please don't say
anything to Shane.
>> I won't.
I can deal with it later,
but not now.
>> Okay.
>> Cirie and I decided Cirie and
Terry, Danielle and I are all
going to vote for Aras.
Shane thinks that I'm going to
do whatever he says and he wants
me to vote Danielle out, and he
wants Cirie to vote Danielle
out.
So I'm going to be dealing with
the wrath of Shane for sure
tonight, and I'm not excited
about it.
(whistling)
>> You kicked my ass.
>> I could have kicked your ass.
>> But we're working this out
so we're gonna make this a joint
effort, okay?
>> Okay. I'm confident with
Courtney and Danielle and I'm
feeling pretty damn good.
We're going to send Aras home,
and with that, we'll have a
three-to-two advantage, and you
know what?
It's gonna be nice.
>> Yeah.
>> What'd you say?
>> Courtney, are you okay?
>> Yeah.
>> You sure?
>> I mean, no, nothing's okay.
>> Right, but I mean, this is
the game, that's it, Danielle,
one, two, three, four.
And we each move on one more
spot.
>> Shane wants to take Courtney
to the final two.
He's told me that.
Terry wants to take Courtney to
the final two.
That, to me, makes Courtney the
most dangerous person out here.
I want to kind of mess up
Terry's plans and mess up
Shane's plans and hopefully we
get rid of Courtney next, and
then it could possibly give me,
Aras and Danielle a little
more leverage in this game.
I just wanted to make sure you
knew exactly what was going on
yesterday.
>> Cirie was quick to fill me
in on the situation.
She really has my back, which
is nice.
She let me know about the
goings-on.
And basically what's going on
now is we're going to vote for
Courtney.
>> But the only way to save you
is to vote Courtney.
But I need to talk to you, too.
>> I'm just trying to see what
would be the best situation for
me.
Would I rather be with Terry,
Courtney, Cirie and I, or would
I rather be with Aras, Cirie
and I?
I'm just trying to see what the
best situation for myself would
be.
>> Well, anyway, we're gonna
have to keep telling Shane that
we're going to vote you.
I swear to God I won't vote you.
And me, you and Aras vote
Courtney because Shane is
gonna vote you.
Terry and Courtney are gonna
vote Aras, and me and you and
Aras are gonna vote Courtney.
Absolutely positive, that's why
you have to let Courtney think
that me, you, her and Terry
are gonna vote Aras.
But if you wouldn't be here
tomorrow, me, you and Aras have
to vote Courtney.
I'm hoping Danielle just stays
strong 'cause Danielle gets
real nervous and it's easy to
turn her.
I'm hoping she just stays calm
tonight and follows through
with the plan.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Austin, Sally...
and Bruce...
(applause)
...returning from a brief stay
in Panama City Hospital.
He'll continue on and be a
member of our jury from here on
out.
Let's talk about the reward
challenge.
Terry, was there some bonding
going on between the three of
you?
>> It was a team bonding, you
know, because we came together
as a team, gave us maybe a
little time to forget the game
and just dig in on a standard
beach barbecue.
So, you know, it was, it was
awesome.
>> PROBST: Cirie, when you hear
Terry say it was nice to put the
game aside for a little bit, do
you buy that?
>> No, please.
I mean, it's a game.
And he may want us to think
that they were just having fun
and barbecuing, but we all know
better.
As long as you're here and your
torch is lit, the game is still
going on.
>> PROBST: So we get to today's
immunity challenge, once again,
Terry wins.
Four individual challenges,
Terry's won four times.
Has anybody started to approach
you and say, "Hey, let's work
something out 'cause you seem
unstoppable"?
>> You know, people aren't
running up to me going, "Hey,
T.D., let's do this, let's do
that," you know?
This tribe has been pretty damn
tight.
So you know what?
The pressure's up; every
immunity challenge I got to
win.
>> PROBST: So, Aras, Casaya
still holding strong.
>> From my perspective, I think
so.
I mean, the reality is tonight
someone from Casaya has to go
home, and I'm fully aware that
the target is nice and large on
my back.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about the
pros and cons of keeping Aras
in the tribe.
On the bad side, you're a
threat.
But on the flip side, if Casaya
is staying strong, you hold the
best chance of defeating Terry.
Fair to say?
>> I think I do have a good
chance of beating Terry, and do
people feel comfortable voting
off the arguably the most
athletic member of the Casaya
five?
I think they have a better
chance with me.
>> PROBST: Shane, what do you
base the vote on when you're
getting rid of one of your own?
Would it be a mistake at this
point in the game to start
thinking about who you want to
take to the final two?
Is it too early for that?
>> Tonight, we have to eat one
of our own, and that's...
Sounds dramatic, but it's going
to be dramatic.
I mean, I know that, like,
people are running stuff in
their head about who they might
want to position themselves to
be around.
We're going to have to shrink a
little bit before the path is
over, for sure.
>> PROBST: How about you,
Danielle?
Thoughts through your head
about this is who I would like
to sit next to in the final two,
and this is who I don't want to
to sit next to?
>> My brain is, like, about to
explode.
I can't stop running numbers in
my head, to be honest with you.
>> PROBST: Courtney, a couple
of challenges ago, you took
a lot of hits.
>> Please, let's get through...!
>> PROBST: You were labeled the
person who wouldn't shut up,
the most annoying, the biggest
poseur.
Do you imagine whether people
would want to take you to final
two or not take you based on the
perception of the tribe of who
you are?
>> Um, I think that when it
comes down to who people want to
take to the final two, I think
that decision has to be made
much further down the line.
I'm not holding onto that
challenge.
I don't think anyone else is.
It's sort of like you're on a
clean slate.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
the vote.
Terry has individual immunity.
Any chance of giving that up to
someone else?
>> Negative.
>> PROBST: There is still the
hidden immunity idol which has
yet to come into play.
If it does, you'll let me know
after the votes are read.
It is time to vote.
Cirie, you're up.
>> This is just a strategic
move.
I can't settle for third or
fourth place after the things
I've heard.
>> You are the ultimate
competitor.
I couldn't have asked for a
better rival, but you are still
the #1 threat.
>> You get to eat as much as
you want, and I will never yell
at you again.
>> You're so beautiful, brother,
but this is for strategy.
Namaste.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Aras.
Danielle.
Aras.
Two votes Aras,
one vote Danielle.
Courtney.
That's one vote Courtney, two
votes Aras, one vote Danielle.
Courtney.
That's two votes Courtney, two
votes Aras, one vote Danielle.
The 11th person voted out of
Survivor, Exile Island:
Courtney.
You need to grab your torch.
>> That was a shocker.
>> PROBST: Courtney, the tribe
has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, after tonight's vote, I
don't think there's any doubt
that this is now an individual
game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> PROBST: Aras and Cirie
cover their tracks.
>> In my viewpoint there is no
choice.
>> PROBST: Aras has had enough.
>> You're starting to offend me.
>> PROBST: And Shane is brought
to his knees.
>> Oh!
>> I'm just completely shocked
right now.
My sisters-- that I
unfortunately trusted-- turned
on me.
I guess they saw me a little
bit too much of a threat for
going to the final two.
But that's the way it goes.
And life goes on from here.
You know, I'm gonna continue
to live my dreams and make it
happen, and that's what matters.