>> PROBST: Tonight, in a
special episode of Survivor
Exile Island, we'll take a
closer look into the
personalities of the survivors
with 13 scenes of all new
footage.
(thunder crashing)
>> Speak up.
That's what I'm saying.
>> I'm saying you have a
negative attitude and it drains
on me, so I stay away from it.
(yelling)
That's bottom flesh.
I intend to keep them all to
myself.
>> (singing in foreign language)
>> She's like, "This is the
girls' soap," you know what I
mean?
And what I wanted to do was look
at her and go, "That's the
lunatics' soap.
>> Yell, get it out.
(yelling)
>> PROBST: We'll also see
highlights of the events that
shaped the first 15 days of
their adventure of a lifetime.
>> Everybody here won't tell you
because they're afraid to tell
you the truth.
>> What are you talking about?
>> I want one, just one.
I just want mine.
>> PROBST: Hunger...
>> Oh, shoot!
>> PROBST: ...thirst...
and violent storms...
>> We're dying, fellas.
>> PROBST: ...push some to the
edge of their capacity to cope.
>> What are you doing?
>> There's no reason for me to
be doing this.
>> PROBST: The misery appeared
to have no end in sight.
>> I figure we've got about
three more days before the
entire tribe can't get out of
bed.
>> PROBST: Exile Island was a
place where some would be
banished to suffer.
And one would find a potential
key to survival in the game.
>> All right!
>> This place breeds bad luck.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> PROBST: 15 days ago, 16
Americans landed on a remote
island off the coast of Panama
to begin the adventure of a
lifetime.
For the first time in Survivor
history they were split into
four tribes.
Younger men versus younger
women, versus the older men
versus the older women.
This is Exile Island.
Throughout this game tribe
members will be banished to this
island.
Wasting not time the tribes
faced off in their first
challenge.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's get it on.
>> PROBST: The losing tribe will
choose one person to stay behind
on Exile Island right off the
bat.
It was a race to find three
amulets and Terry, Austin and
Ruth Marie came out on top.
Danielle finished last and the
younger women picked Misty to
stay behind.
Then another twist was revealed.
Hidden somewhere on this island
is an immunity idol.
Along the way you'll be given
clues as to the whereabouts of
that idol.
>> Ooh, hoo.
>> PROBST: Arriving at their
camp, the older women thrived
under the leadership of Tina.
>> The older women are
performing very well.
Tina-- she's a very, very
resourceful woman.
>> More of that stuff, keep 'er
going.
>> Good job, good job.
>> PROBST: The young men's start
was not quite as strong.
>> You tell me when you start of
feel a little bit of energy.
>> Our tribe's just hysterical.
I mean, we all established
within two hours of being here
we don't have a clue what we
were doing.
That's a shelter right there,
gentlemen.
>> We don't want to peak the
first night.
>> PROBST: While at the younger
women's camp, in this never
before seen footage, it was a
struggle just to open a coconut.
>> I don't think there's coconut
juice in here.
>> I hear it.
Let's crack one open.
>> We should.
Doesn't seem like very much.
>> Oh, no.
>> The machete is a bit tricky.
I'm shocked by how badly I'm
doing opening coconuts.
Damn.
>> No, wait, wait, wait.
Go like...
>> Really?
I always open coconuts from the
front.
>> We were all expecting I think
a male to be here to help us out
with that department.
>> All right, you try.
We'll take turns.
>> Just don't come too close to
me because I'm dangerous with a
machete.
Ready...
>> Oh, that's it.
Now do that against the wood.
>> I love the machete.
I worked construction for a
summer and favorite part was
demolition.
And maybe that's that side of me
coming out.
>> Gosh, this is so easy.
>> Yeah.
>> Gosh.
>> Those little coconuts-- they
are hard.
But I love taking that machete
and just going to town on
whatever I can.
And it worked.
I broke some coconuts.
>> Our first coconut.
We drink from the same coconut,
man, yeah.
>> PROBST: At the older men's
camp, everything was under
control...
>> That's the best smelling
stinking fire I've seen in a
long time.
>> PROBST: ...leaving time for
Dan the astronaut and Terry the
fighter pilot to make a pact.
>> I'll never lie to you.
>> Okay.
>> I expect you to never lie to
me.
>> I'll shake on that.
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> PROBST: Shane however, was
wearing down quickly.
>> We're here... all four of us
don't know to get the water.
All four of us don't need to
head to the path to find the mud
chute.
I'm exhausted, I haven't had a
cigarette, and I smoke three
packs of cigarettes a day for
20 years and I haven't had a
cigarette in like 31 hours.
I mean, I'm just at the end of
my rope.
>> PROBST: Later that day, Tina
made a valuable discovery.
>> Holy criminy.
An oyster.
Ah.
I just caught an oyster.
It's just like embedded in
there.
That thing has been embedded in
there for millions of years I
think.
Oh, my God, look at that.
That is a lot of flesh.
That's probably enough to keep
me going for the day.
I think it was the best oyster I
ever had in my life.
It was beautiful.
I love oysters.
(purring)
Oh, there's another one.
And another one.
Got a couple lunches here.
I did not tell anyone that I
found oysters.
I intend to keep them all for
myself.
And if you saw where I found
them, there's no way they're
going to know they're there.
>> PROBST: That night at the
older men's camp, Bruce had
trouble sleeping and he put
his idle time to good use.
>> Sometimes when things are
bothering me late at night I
like to break away and just do
my karate.
My karate practice is very
important to me, 'cause it
always keeps me in shape and
keeps my mind focused.
I take my mind off everything
else.
I focus on each karate move.
Usually executing a kata--
my ancient form movement.
Usually fighting three or four
imaginary opponents.
Sometimes I practice 100 at a
time.
>> Bruce wants to come down here
and get his Miyagi on in front
of the water and karate down.
I'm cool with that.
I like odd people.
I think he's got a lot of
anxiety about being here and,
uh, I think that's probably how
he, you know, gets it out.
>> When I'm doing my kata, I
always feel like I'm trying to
destroy my opponent.
So I have to keep that karate as
part of my game plan.
>> PROBST: On day two, Misty
came up with a plan regarding
the hidden immunity idol.
>> I'm the first one voted off
should we not win.
Which would make sense if I was
in their shoes.
So when I see my tribe mates at
the next immunity challenge,
I'll trick them into thinking
that I found the immunity idol.
>> PROBST: At the first immunity
challenge, Misty rejoined her
tribe and implied that she had
found the idol.
So, Misty, how's Exile Island?
>> You told us there was an
immunity idol on there and you
told us where it was, so...
>> PROBST: So you spent a little
time looking for it?
>> Enough.
>> PROBST: During the challenge,
the younger men fell behind
early.
Young guys still trying to get
that rope free.
Young guys in serious trouble.
While the younger women and the
older men cruised.
Younger women have immunity!
Older men win immunity.
>> We got it, we got it, we got
it.
>> PROBST: Down to two tribes.
One immunity left.
Older women, younger guys.
In the end, the younger men
passed the older women for the
last piece of immunity.
>> Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Younger men win
immunity!
Older women going to Tribal
Council.
After the challenge, Misty
arrived at her camp for the
first time.
>> I love it, you guys.
This is beautiful.
>> Well, when Misty came back
from Exile Island, we were
extremely anxious to know if
she'd gotten the idol or not.
>> What did you do out there?
You were just like...
>> Digging.
>> She was a digging fool.
>> You digged both days?
>> I dig... I dug... yeah.
Until yesterday afternoon.
>> Like digging?
>> Yeah, my whole focus was
like, dig, dig, dig.
>> And it worked out, I mean,
you said you found it, so...
>> It's that whole don't tell
anyone if you have it or don't
have it thing.
>> I don't know why you need to
keep it quiet.
>> I tried to trick them into
thinking that I had the immunity
idol.
I think Courtney called my
bluff-- rightly so.
I think she's very good at
deceiving people.
So I think she could see it in
me, 'cause I'm really not that
great at it.
>> How long did you have to dig
before you found it?
>> All day.
>> You found it today?
>> No, it was yesterday and I
was sitting there...
Yeah, no, girl.
You think?
>> I don't know-- she had a good
story.
She could have it.
I don't want her to pull this
out of her hat later down the
road, when immunity could be
really worth something.
>> Misty came back and told all
of us that she had found the
immunity idol.
And I didn't buy it for a
second, but the other girls
seemed to buy it.
>> PROBST: Facing Tribal
Council, Tina's tribemates were
put off by her isolated
behavior.
But Tina's behavior was
misunderstood.
>> I wrote this in the sand for
my son, Charlie, who was killed
in a car accident just, you
know, four-and-a-half months
ago.
And he was just 16 years old.
So, I will come and talk to him
once in a while... alone.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, Cirie was
worried about her place in the
game.
>> I'm really nervous 'cause I
don't want to be the first one
to go.
>> PROBST: So she set her sights
on getting rid of Tina.
(yelling)
>> PROBST: But Tina caught a
fish, complicating the tribe's
decision.
>> I do think that Cirie's the
weak link.
There are a hundred reasons to
keep Tina.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Tina's outdoor skills were not
enough to save her and she
became the first person voted
off Survivor: Exile Island.
Tina, the tribe has spoken.
>> I think that if the dynamics
had been different and we would
have had the full eight people,
I'd still be there because the
men would have taken me for my
strength and power and knowledge
of living in the wild.
>> PROBST: That night, a heavy
downpour hit the camps...
(thunder crashing)
...and Bruce caused a small
storm of his own.
>> Yeah, yeah, Bruce, go down to
the ocean.
>> Calm down.
>> I'm upset because
Bruce used our drinking water to
wash his hands, and we have,
like, a half a bottle of
drinking water left.
That's unacceptable, especially
when there's a downpour
happening and you can just step
outside and wash your hands in
the downpour.
You can't be, you can't be doing
that.
You can if you want to get voted
off.
(thunder crashing)
>> PROBST: Despite the
relentless downpour, the younger
women found new ways to keep
their spirits up in this new
footage from morning four.
>> We should learn a Spanish
song.
>> That would be great.
>> Okay, so...
(singing in Spanish)
>> Yeah!
So, it's, like...
"On the island of women
with my sisters of Bayoneta."
(speaking Spanish)
"But still there's a smile
in the soul."
>> I like that one.
>> So, you guys repeat.
>> Okay.
(singing in Spanish)
>> It feels great that there's
four of us now.
We're all, like, content
individuals, even though we
don't really have anything.
They're into, like, learning new
songs from foreign lands and,
like, they're just cool.
Cool women.
I'm just so happy to be here
with them.
(singing in Spanish)
>> The four of us were just
huddled together, soaking wet,
just singing some songs, so it
kinda warmed us up.
It's so crazy to be here and,
like, be hungry and cold and
tired and be having so much fun.
(singing in Spanish)
>> I like that!
>> You guys got it!
>> Isn't it fun?
>> PROBST: But over at the
older men's camp, Shane was
struggling to keep his head in
the game.
>> You know, I think about
everything that I'm missing
right now.
I think about my kid, and you
know, there's no... there's no
reason for me to be doing
this.
No more torrential downpours,
Sir God.
No more of those!
(thunder crashes)
>> PROBST: Later that day, the
four tribes met for a reward
challenge.
>> Green sweats.
>> PROBST: In a schoolyard
pick...
>> Cool guy.
>> PROBST: ...the four tribes
became two: La Mina and Casaya.
Bruce was not picked and he was
banished to Exile Island, but
with an unusual twist.
You are the only person
guaranteed to be safe at the
next Tribal Council.
>> Yeah! Thank you!
>> PROBST: Well, go.
The boat's out there.
The two tribes then squared off
for fishing gear.
Survivors ready! Go!
In a brutal challenge, La Mina
pulled out a narrow victory.
La Mina wins reward!
Arriving at the new Casaya beach
after the challenge...
...Shane quickly set up an
alliance with Danielle, Courtney
and Aras.
>> I go on the beach and I was
right there.
I was, like, "Here it is.
You, you, you, you, let's lock
in right now.
(laughter)
I'm serious.
>> PROBST: At the new La Mina
camp, Terry was busy making an
alliance of his own.
>> Dan and I were talking that
we'd like to make a bond with
you guys.
It's, it's in our best interest,
probably.
What do you think?
>> It makes a lot of sense.
>> PROBST: The next day at
Casaya, desperate times led to
desperate measures.
>> We're not really doing really
well, honestly.
I mean, we do not have fire, we
don't have water because we
don't have fire.
>> Just that little bit is,
like, so refreshing.
>> We were all dehydrated, some
more so than others.
Courtney and Daniel have not had
water for five days.
Maybe these people can rise to
the occasions.
I know they're all competitors.
Maybe that's gonna happen.
I don't know.
We'll just have to see.
>> PROBST: At Exile Island,
Bruce battled the elements.
On day six, La Mina set out with
their newly won fishing gear.
>> I saw some fish just right
over there.
>> PROBST: ...but suffered a
major setback when Sally lost
the spear.
>> I have some bad news.
>> What?
>> I lost that spear.
>> Did you try to go back down
with the mask?
>> Yeah. It was so deep.
>> I'm very frustrated about the
spear.
I had no doubt in my mind we
would be eating tons of fish if
we had that spear.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Terry carried La Mina
to victory, virtually
single-handedly.
Terry hauling that anchor in!
La Mina wins immunity!
After the challenge, at Casaya,
Shane wanted to quit.
>> Hey, what are you doing?
>> If somebody wants to quit,
let 'em quit!
>> PROBST: But Aras talked Shane
into sticking around...
>> Just try it, okay?
>> Okay, all right.
>> PROBST: ...putting Cirie and
Melinda at risk.
>> I don't care which one of you
goes.
Like, whoever doesn't go now is
going next.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Bruce returned from Exile Island
and watched as Melinda became
the second person voted off
Survivor: Exile Island.
Melinda, the tribe has spoken.
>> It's a hundred-times harder
than you could ever possibly
think it's gonna be.
Sure, you know, it's all gonna
be over in 39 days, but 39 days
sounds like a lot less time when
you're at home on the couch than
when you're laying on bamboo.
>> PROBST: That night after
Tribal Council, Bruce became a
member of the Casaya Tribe,
and his impact was immediate.
>> So this is what we're gonna
do: we're gonna filter water
through three T-shirts, double
layer.
That's gonna be 90% pure water.
>> I know that I was the last
man picked, now I'm emerging as
the top of the tribe.
It's the best bottle so far.
>> PROBST: The next morning at
the reward challenge, Casaya
acknowledged Bruce's positive
effect on the tribe.
>> I feel a hell of a lot
better.
>> We got Bruce dawg with us.
He helps us, man.
>> Bruce is a savior.
>> PROBST: But his presence
wasn't enough to beat out a
sure-handed La Mina.
>> Fire at will.
>> Come on. Get it, Aras!
>> PROBST: Terry makes an
unbelievable catch!
La Mina wins reward!
La Mina was on a roll.
(all cheer)
For the first time, the winner
sent a member of the losers to
Exile Island.
(all whispering)
Who are you sending?
>> Bruce, we're sending you
back.
>> PROBST: And Bruce was forced
to return to Exile Island.
>> You guys are playing for
keeps, huh?
>> PROBST: That night, after the
challenge, things began to
deteriorate at Casaya.
In this never-before-seen
footage, frustration over losing
boiled to the surface.
>> We made a tactical error at
the challenge.
>> Like today, I said, "I'm a
wide receiver.
I should be catching."
>> Yeah, but that's all you
said.
>> What else is there to say?
>> Speak up, that's what I'm
saying.
"Guys, I'm not a good swimmer.
Guys, I'm hurt. I can't do this.
"I'm not gonna be able to put my
100%."
>> It seemed like someone else
had, like, a personal interest
in being there.
Like you wanted to out there and
have the point.
I was, like, "You know what?
Let me step back."
>> Whew! The fireworks started.
These are the craziest, sickest,
aggravatingest, people that I
have ever been around in my
life.
We don't have a team.
It's the reason why we're not
winning.
>> I've seen four people walk
down to the beach by themselves.
What am I supposed to do?
Run up to 'em, "Hey, guys, what
are you talking about, guys?"
>> Hey, so let's get to what
you're really bummed out about.
You're bummed out 'cause you're
on the outside.
>> No, I'm bummed out that you
guys act like seventh-grade
girls.
>> We act like seventh-grade
girls?
>> Yeah.
>> What am I, what am I doing,
act like a seventh-grade girl,
homey?
>> When you throw your little
tantrums over here, that's why I
stay away from you guys.
Like, Courtney's, like, Miss
Negativity.
Like, we're supposed to be this
grownup-type family?
>> This is my fault?
>> I'm not saying it's your
fault.
I'm saying you have a negative
attitude and it drains on me, so
I stay away from you.
>> Why would it benefit me?
What group?
>> The group; all of us.
>> The group of four?
>> Communication skills in most
of this tribe are horrible.
Bobby's really upset because he
knows he's on the outside of
this four-person alliance and
he doesn't know how to say that,
so he just comes up with
different reasons to be upset
with people.
>> Instead of continuing this
negativity, because it's not
going to end, we're never going
to come to a resolution about
it.
>> Yeah, we are.
>> Okay, so right now, all that
negativity everybody has, get it
out.
(yelling)
>> Let it go.
We need to... I don't give a
damn what everybody else thinks.
This game at this point is a
team game.
So all of us need to come
together as a group.
I think a lot of people in this
tribe are acting very
immaturely.
I've played team sports my whole
life and this is the worst team
I've ever been a part of.
>> I think you need to lead the
discussion, and then when you
say, "Listen, be quiet, I've
heard everybody.
Let's make a decision," then we
need to just all shut up and
respect that.
We need leadership when we're
deciding challenges.
>> One of the good things that
came out of that argument was
that we decided that I would be
our leader at challenges.
Now a win could change the
morale.
If we win this, we're, you know,
everyone knows we're back in it.
Each one of us has to overcome
our personal differences.
Compete and be willing to work
together.
>> We're going to be fine.
(thunder crashing)
>> PROBST: On day eight, Casaya
was coming apart at the seams.
It's Shane's thinking seat.
It's mine for the rest of
the... please, actually, could
no one else sit on my thinking
seat, please?
>> Why does it have to be yours?
>> Because I picked it.
You want this one, I'll go get
another one!
I want one, this one!
If you want this one, I'll go
get another one!
I just want mine.
>> With Courtney and Shane
there's always something.
The funny thing is, these are
the people that you guys decided
to align with.
>> PROBST: Later in the day, in
this new scene, the food
situation at Casaya was reaching
a critical stage.
>> I'm so weak from not eating.
This is fun.
>> We haven't eaten anything
today.
That is the killer.
Whatever is the next five levels
up from hungry, that's what we
are.
>> There's a snake.
Hey, guys, come look at this.
If it's a boa, we can eat that
thing, man.
>> Are you sure it's a boa?
>> Yes.
>> You're positive?
>> I'm 100% positive.
>> That's snake dinner, bro.
>> Snake dinner right here.
Who wants snake?
>> You know, snake for many
people means transformation
and even healing.
The snakes that go up on the
medicine-- you know how
they're represented there.
Snakes are like power,
transformation, healing, and as
we eat it, let's just take in
snake energy, because we're
eating snake.
>> Yo, don't eat it yet.
Snake, according to Courtney is
transformational...
>> If Courtney says snakes
represent togetherness, I'm
willing to listen.
As long as it's going to keep me
in the group, then hey, to
togetherness with the snake.
I don't care.
>> Here's to transformation.
>> Transformation.
Transform us.
>> Tastes like chicken.
>> You stole my line.
>> Thank the snake for giving us
his life.
Thank you, snake.
>> I'm eating snake!
>> PROBST: Bruce returned from
Exile Island joining Casaya for
a bruising immunity challenge.
>> Ow!
>> PROBST: After a hard fought
battle, Casaya put an end to La
Mina's winning streak.
At Tribal Council the vote went
against Misty.
Third person voted out of
Survivor Exile Island, Misty.
Misty, that's enough votes.
One question left, did you find
the immunity idol?
>> No, I did not.
>> PROBST: And Misty became
the third person voted off
Survivor Exile Island.
Misty, the tribe has spoken.
>> I actually was very shocked
that I was the first one to go
from my tribe.
I knew there was a boys' club
going on.
I just didn't think that I would
be the first female to go.
So I was surprised, and
disappointed definitely, very
disappointed.
>> PROBST: The next morning at
Casaya, Shane was having regrets
about leaving his son.
>> Today is my son's birthday.
He's 13 today.
He's a teenager.
And I probably shouldn't have
missed that.
I probably should have not come
here.
My son's name is Boston, and we
have an unbelievably special
relationship.
I was 21 when I had him.
And the thing about this game is
that you really start to learn
and understand what's
important.
And I realize I've learned a lot
about myself, and a lot about
what I want to do with my life
now-- which is just be close
to the people that I love.
>> You're the best dad in the
world.
You've got your son's name on
your heart.
>> Not the best dad in the
world.
I'm the best dad in the world
for him.
But I've been talking... I've
been talking to him all day.
>> Good.
>> Yeah.
We could sing him "Happy
Birthday."
>> That's what I was thinking.
>>  Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Boston
Happy birthday to you.
(cheering)
>> Singing "Happy Birthday" to
Boston did make us feel more
like a unit, like a family
almost.
And it was really nice.
Even if it was just for those
few minutes.
Because believe me, it's not
going to last.
Not with this tribe.
>> PROBST: At La Mina...
...Dan brought Ruth Marie into
the men's alliance... leaving
Sally on the outside looking in.
>> All I can do right now is
keep working hard and prove
myself valuable.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: A fully stocked
bathroom was on the line.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Go!
In a close race...
Both sides solving the puzzle.
...Casaya pulled out the
victory.
>> Right there.
>> PROBST: Casaya wins reward!
>> Yeah, baby!
>> PROBST: And Terry was
banished to Exile Island.
When Casaya returned to camp...
>> Beautiful.
>> PROBST: ...things turned sour
over the use of the outhouse.
>> My vote is to use the
bathroom for firewood and just
keeping things dry.
>> Anybody mind if I break in
the dumpster?
>> Use the bathroom to keep
the wood dry.
Bobby just frustrates me.
I can't stand the fact that he's
not a gentleman.
>> I'm about ten pounds lighter.
>> PROBST: At La Mina, Austin
took the time to get to know
Sally.
>> I was the kid who did
everything by the book.
Everything I did was, like,
right.
>> I can see that.
>> And so, going through the
whole divorce-- it was like the
first time I crossed my parents.
There's a lot of shame that
comes in with that.
>> ...and I'm so sorry.
>> It's just really sad.
It's just such a waste.
Life is so short.
>> Sally and I had a really good
conversation.
She's going through some tough
times in her life right now.
Her parents come from a very
strict Christian background.
And because Sally got a divorce,
they have all but kind of cut
ties with her.
>> I can't regret any of that.
And, uh...
>> It's so hard to believe that,
they're that black and white.
>> The hardest thing for me has
been what the divorce has done
to my relationship with my
parents and how, you know, it's
gone through some turmoil.
I know they love me.
>> It's eating away at them,
I'll guarantee.
>> Yeah, I know they love me, I
know they miss me.
My parents don't know how to
support me in this decision
right now.
I have hope that someday that's
going to change and you know,
our relationship is going to be
closer.
But they're needing some space
right now, and you know, it's
just hard.
>> Sally and I have become
close.
I just think that she's an
extraordinary person.
I don't want to see Sally go.
Maybe I'll shop my idea to keep
Sally around.
But I got a hunch it's going to
be just like the fish out here
in this ocean, man-- no nibbles,
no bites.
>> PROBST: On, Exile Island,
Terry deciphered the clues...
>> Why has fate chose you to be
the first one out here?
Why?
>> PROBST: ...and found the
immunity idol.
>> Beautiful.
"This talisman can be used to
keep you safe from the vote at
Tribal Council." All right!
>> PROBST: While Terry
celebrated, the Casaya foursome
was falling apart.
>> What?
>> An aversion to working?
>> Oh, okay. That's nice.
>> No, I'm just telling ya, I
think everyone has the same
opinion.
>> What do you do?
Do you get water?
You ever gotten water?
Alls you do is ask people to get
fire for you so you can ... do
the fire.
That's all you do.
>> What do I do?
>> That's all you do!
>> I hunt every day, I go and
get as much wood as you do.
>> I don't help you guys catch
food?
>> I go and get as much wood as
you do.
>> I get wood. I go for water.
I help you guys get snails.
And for you to say it like
that...
>> And everybody here won't tell
you because they're afraid to
tell you the truth!
>> What are you talking about?
>> Danielle, Shane and Courtney,
Aras foursome is like some
psychotic joke.
And it seems to be unraveling
little by little.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Terry returned from
Exile Island.
Survivors ready. Go!
And despite Sally's strong
performance...
Sally running across the beams.
...Casaya again came out on top.
Casaya wins immunity!
(all cheering)
Sally was slated to be sent home
next at La Mina.
>> It's a shame to pack up my
stuff and leave here with so
much left to offer this tribe.
>> PROBST: But Austin made an
appeal to Terry.
>> We got to have our strongest
team.
>> PROBST: And at Tribal
Council, Austin's efforts to
keep Sally paid off.
The men broke their alliance
with Ruth Marie, who became the
fourth person voted off
Survivor: Exile Island.
Ruth Marie, the tribe has
spoken.
>> I really thought I had an
alliance with four gentlemen.
But it's not a game of honor.
It's a game of deception.
So they didn't do anything
wrong.
>> PROBST: The next morning, the
fire caused sparks at Casaya in
this new scene from day 12.
>> Pretty much everybody but
Bobby is working.
Bobby doesn't ever catch any
food, never gets any water.
He doesn't even try to help get
the fire going.
For his size, he should have...
I feel like he should have more
strength.
(laughing)
(yawning)
>> Bob.
Bob...
You feel okay?
>> Yeah, I'm cool.
>> Yeah.
Danielle, apparently in her
fatigued and dumb state,
apparently thought I was
serious.
She apparently thought I really
couldn't figure out that I was
supposed to be putting the stick
on the fire.
She apparently thought I was
serious.
Just like completely over her
head, like all this stuff is
just, like... just gone.
>> Here, let me do it, I'll do
it.
Bobby takes a twig.
"Where do I put this?"
And he did it, he said it, like,
six times.
Finally, I got so aggravated, I
go, "You know what, Bobby, I'll
do it.
Forget it, forget it, go back to
bed."
We figured he's a guy, I mean,
guys should be good at that,
that he would get it going.
And he didn't give me anything.
He just picked up and went back
to bed.
I don't know, me and him just
don't click.
We just don't get along.
>> PROBST: In this new footage
from day 12 at Casaya, soap from
an earlier reward was finally
put to use.
>> Thank God for that bar of
soap.
>> I mean, it almost makes you
feel like a different person.
We won in the reward challenge,
three bars of soap, a
back scrubber...
After ten days of not washing
any part of your body, it felt
great.
>> Danielle and I just wanted to
have a girls' bar of soap and a
guys' bar of soap.
So far, Bruce has been the first
one to use the backscratcher,
you know.
And Bruce has the soap, and
it's like, covered in black
hairs.
And just to let the boys know,
the soap that's wrapped like
this is the girls' soap.
I get kind of grossed out
easily.
>> What, you want the girls to
use a bar and the boys to use a
bar?
>> Yeah, the girls to use a bar
and the guys to use a bar.
>> Well, the guys have two bars.
We'll use one.
>> We're out here, we're like
sharing everything.
Courtney's, like, this is the
girls' soap, you know what I
mean?
And what I wanted to do was look
at her and go, "That's the
lunatics' soap."
>> Ugh!
>> It's nasty.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, the tribes competed
for food and wine.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: La Mina took the
lead.
Terry with a nice grab.
Bruce really having trouble.
But Sally struggled and Bobby
chopped his way to victory for
Casaya.
Casaya wins reward!
>> We eat!
>> PROBST: And they won a bounty
of fish and wine before they
picked Terry to go back to Exile
Island.
>> Good luck, Terry.
Casaya returned to a waterlogged
camp.
>> This is a nightmare.
>> We have a ton of fish, but we
can't cook it.
Everything is wet.
>> PROBST: But even without
fire, they manage to make the
most of their reward.
>> I've never eaten raw fish.
I hope I don't wake up in the
morning with some kind of
sickness or something.
(thunder)
>> PROBST: That night, Bruce and
Bobby spent the night in the
outhouse with each other and the
last bottle of wine.
In the morning, the missing
bottle did not go unnoticed.
>> Someone would have to pour
it down my throat for me to
drink the last bottle of wine
that we as a tribe won.
>> You really made a bad, bad
call.
>> I don't feel bad that I stole
your wine.
Like, I feel bad that I deprived
them of wine, but I have no hard
feelings whatsoever about the
fact that you've been deprived
of wine.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
La Mina with a big lead.
La Mina finally put an end to
their losing streak.
La Mina has it!
La Mina wins immunity!
At Tribal Council, Bobby paid
the price for drinking the last
of the wine and he was the fifth
person voted off Survivor: Exile
Island.
Bobby, the tribe has spoken.
>> I was kind of mixed up with a
bunch of little jokers that, you
know, pretty much had it in for
me from the get-go.
In a game like this, you get
enough weaklings together, they
can form a pretty strong block.
>> PROBST: The following
morning, Shane wanted out of the
alliance he had built on the
promise of his son's name.
>> I want to ask you guys if I
can take my son's name...
>> Done.
>> Done?
>> PROBST: Fed up with Shane's
antics, the girls agreed
immediately.
>> Well, if that's how you feel
about it, then fine.
Get out of the alliance, you're
off anyway.
See ya later. Bye.
Out.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, at La
Mina, Sally knew her days were
numbered.
>> It's been a rough couple of
days.
The four guys were kind of doing
like a boys club thing.
But I think it's short sighted.
>> PROBST: At a high stakes
challenge for reward and
immunity, there was an
unexpected twist.
The person you send to Exile
Island will not go to Tribal
Council tonight.
That means they cannot be voted
out.
Terry's back with the last
puzzle piece.
La Mina took an early lead.
Dan and Sally quickly getting to
work.
But when Dan and Sally struggled
on the puzzle, Casaya...
>> Step on it! Step on it!
>> PROBST: ...put the pieces
together for the victory.
Casaya wins reward and immunity!
Casaya, who's it going to be?
>> Sally.
>> PROBST: When Casaya chose
Sally to go to Exile Island, it
meant the end of the game for
one of the remaining four La
Mina men.
>> I'm so happy right now.
>> PROBST: Casaya reveled in the
glory of a Panamanian feast.
>> I just ate everything in
sight.
>> PROBST: With bellies full of
food, their tribal wounds began
to heal.
>> And I apologize, okay?
>> Accepted.
>> PROBST: But Cirie was not
happy with the rediscovered
harmony.
>> I almost wanted to lose,
because I really felt that Shane
was going.
But now... everybody's all in
love again.
Damn!
>> PROBST: With Sally safe on
Exile Island, the La Mina men
had to make a difficult
decision at Tribal Council.
And Dan became the sixth person
voted off Survivor: Exile
Island.
Dan, the tribe has spoken.
>> As the days went on, even
though the hunger grew and the
deprivation grew, the sense of
being part of nature also grew.
It was beautiful and I was not
ready to go home.
>> PROBST: Where 16 once stood,
only ten remain.
What will happen as the rewards
get bigger?
The risks get greater?
Whoa, easy guys.
>> We have a medical emergency.
>> PROBST: And one could be
forced to leave the game.
Join us next time as the
adventure continues.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
New blood changes everything.
>> Hey, come here quickly.
>> We're home, baby.
I'm ready to get in there, see
if I can come out victorious.
>> You come over and we will go
to the final five.
>> PROBST: Terry wheels and
deals.
>> I'm just looking for two
people to swing the total game
our way.
>> PROBST: And Bruce gets
whacked.
>> I just hit Bruce in the face
with a machete, I'm out of here.
>> So you guys want to come with
a... our mantra?
>> I think we need to do Bobby's
King's Ransom.
>> More like this.
There are several poses.
The King's Ransom.
Dah.
After The King's Ransom comes
the Double Dragon.
And then there's The Warrior's
Honor.
Piece them all together...
Bah, bah, dah, wooh-wooh.