>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
With Sally alone on Exile
Island...
>> Oh, wow!
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> Give me some paddle.
>> PROBST: The La Mina men were
set to merge with Casaya.
>> We're down six-four.
If we don't get somebody to
switch over right away, we'll
just get picked off.
>> There they are.
>> PROBST: The Casaya Six saw
them coming...
>> Hey! Come here quickly!
>> PROBST: ...and immediately
circled up against them.
>> We stay together, we get to
the top six.
One, two, three.
>> Come on in!
>> PROBST: The men were
welcomed, and Sally soon joined
them.
The former rivals briefly put
the game aside.
>> Oh, fruit!
>> Chocolate!
>> It was a very cordial
gathering, but I could sense
there probably was a little bit
of sizing up.
>> PROBST: Terry went to work
on a new shelter.
>> What's Terry building?
We'll vote him off.
>> He might be on the chopping
block.
>> PROBST: Then Terry went to
work on Bruce.
>> You come over, and we will go
to the final five.
>> PROBST: Then Shane.
>> Hi, Shane.
>> PROBST: Then Cirie.
>> Our group of four would like
to offer you more time of
worry-free life around here.
>> It was almost laughable.
I don't think he's in a
position to offer me anything.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Cirie first down!
One by one, the former Casaya
members confidently dropped,
leaving Nick, Austin and Terry
to battle it out.
>> Terry, no!
>> No way, hoss.
Hang in there.
Austin's struggling to hang in
there.
>> PROBST: Austin's out.
Terry's determination paid off.
Nick drops out.
Terry wins the first individual
immunity.
>> Bruce!
>> PROBST: Back at camp, Shane
made it obvious who was in
control.
>> I'm very proud of us for
staying together.
>> PROBST: As the two strongest
former La Mina men, Nick and
Austin were the targets.
>> Nick seems like Terry #2.
>> I don't know why I feel like
Austin's the call.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council...
Let's talk about the immunity
challenge today.
Austin thought he was gone, so
he spoke openly about faking
weakness at the challenge.
>> I opted to come down, and I'm
probably going to pay the price
for that.
>> PROBST: The strategy was
appear weak?
>> Something along those lines.
>> PROBST: But, when the votes
were read...
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor.
...Austin was spared, and Nick
was sent home.
Nick, the tribe has spoken.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> I feel great.
Here another day, my man.
I'm here another day.
>> During Tribal Council last
night, Austin was, like, "Oh,
well, I tanked that challenge on
purpose so that I didn't look
too strong."
I was, like, oh, my gosh, what
have we done?
I just felt like the wrong guy
went.
>> My mouth kept dropping each
time.
Yesterday, I thought I had come
off with the greatest caper of
all time.
But when it looked like it
wasn't working, and I'm going
home, I wanted everyone to at
least know, "Hey, I could have
hung a little bit longer, guys."
Now, in retrospect, that was so
stupid to let them know my
plan because now I'm afraid
people are questioning whether
they really trust me.
>> These snails are like members
of La Mina: slimy and hard to
get out.
>> Oh, Aras, aren't you being
cutthroat?
>> No. They're cutthroat, and
Austin is a slimeball.
>> He's a slimeball.
>> A slimeball.
>> Yeah, you're right.
I can't trust him.
That's for sure.
>> He's going to try to work
everybody.
The one thing we have to make
sure is that we don't reveal
anything, period.
>> Today's a new day, and new
numbers are rolling through my
head.
Casaya-- they're sitting there
all happy because they have the
numbers.
But if I can draw two of those
people over on our side, the
tables could turn.
I'm still a team guy.
I'm still a La Mina guy versus
the remaining Casaya members,
and I'm hoping to turn it
around a little bit, and we'll
see what happens.
There's always hope.
>> Tree mail!
It's going to be a fun one.
Here. Ready?
"Skill can win a boat race, and
making tough decisions takes
some guts.
But, in political battles,
you'll always deal with nuts."
>> All political.
>> Tree mail said something
about making political
decisions and, as far as Austin
and Terry and I go, that's a
good challenge to have come our
way at this point.
>> Yay! It sounds like a fun
one, doesn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> We're hoping that maybe it
will create some conflict for
the original Casaya members and
shake things up a little bit
around here.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah. Ready.
>> PROBST: It is for reward.
Here's how it works.
We're going to divide into
three teams.
Each team will have one boat
and 100 coconuts.
On my go, you're going to race
to take your coconuts and put
them in the boats of the other
two teams.
The more you put into another
team's boat, the more it's
going to slow them down later.
Keep in mind, while you're doing
this to their boat, they're
doing it to your boat.
Once you're rid of all your
coconuts, get in your boat,
paddle out, retrieve a tribe
flag and a fishing net, then
make your way back to shore.
You'll use the fishing net to
now carry all the coconuts that
the other teams have put into
your boat back up the beach,
put them in the bin.
First tribe to get all the
coconuts in their bin, get on
their finish map with the tribe
flag, wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For the winning tribe
of three, you'll be picked up
tomorrow by boat, taken to a
lovely little spot where you
will find a bed and breakfast
waiting for you.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Bacon, eggs, mimosas.
In addition, the winning team
of three will decide who goes
to Exile Island.
All right.
We're going to randomly divide
into teams.
We'll get started.
There are three teams:
Shane, Terry, Austin.
Bruce, Aras and Sally.
Danielle, Courtney, Cirie.
Here we go, for reward, a
breakfast in bed!
Survivors ready?
Go!
Trying to get all of your
coconuts in somebody else's
boat.
You drop a coconut, you have to
pick it up.
Austin hunched over, moving
quickly.
Terry and Aras right behind him.
Get those coconuts in the boat
as quickly as you can, and get
back!
Austin and Terry unload into
Cirie, Danielle and Courtney's
boat.
Aras going to load up on Terry,
Shane and Austin.
Danielle loses one.
That's going to slow her down.
The sooner you unload your
coconuts, the faster you paddle
out and get back.
Aras, Austin and Terry coming
with a lot of coconuts.
Who are they targeting?
Austin and Terry are going
after the girls.
Aras is heading right back to
Terry, Shane and Austin's boat.
Figured out a good strategy,
ganging up on the three guys.
>> Danielle, stay in their boat.
We're not putting in any in
yours.
>> PROBST: Aras and Danielle on
opposite teams, but talking
together.
Danielle loading up on the guys.
More coconuts you put in their
boat, the tougher it's going
to be.
Courtney with more coconuts for
Terry, Austin and Shane.
Everybody following the lead of
Aras.
Austin going to give Aras,
Sally and Bruce some of his
coconuts.
Terry heads to the same place.
Bruce having trouble.
Coconuts all over the place.
>> Bruce, take your time.
We've got a lead.
Don't worry about it.
>> PROBST: The girls have a lot
of coconuts left.
They're falling behind.
You can't paddle out until your
coconut bin is empty.
Aras and Bruce unloading on
Terry, Austin and Shane.
Austin coming down.
Terry and Shane getting the
last coconuts for their team.
Sally coming down.
>> Last trip!
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Last trip for Aras,
Sally and Bruce.
Terry and Shane with the last
coconuts for their team.
Aras right behind.
Terry, Shane and Austin heading
out!
Sally, Aras and Bruce are rid
of their last coconuts.
They're heading out.
>> Come on, let's go! Come on!
>> PROBST: Terry, Shane and
Austin right behind!
The girls are so far behind
they have to put their coconuts
in their own boat.
>> Come on! We're good!
We're good! Keep going!
>> PROBST: Aras, Sally, Bruce
close to their flag and
their fishnet.
Shane, Austin, Terry trying to
make up some ground.
Aras, Sally and Bruce have their
flag and their net.
They're heading back.
Shane has the flag.
Shane has the net.
They're heading back.
Danielle, Cirie, Courtney
falling farther and farther
behind.
No shot in this challenge.
Aras, Sally, Bruce paddling
back.
Shane, Austin and Terry
paddling back.
Going to be a race back to
shore.
Aras dives in.
Shane right behind.
Both teams clipping in.
Start unloading coconuts!
>> Austin, up here.
>> PROBST: You've got to use
the fishing net to put the
coconuts in.
Terry throwing coconuts
everywhere.
Austin trying to keep track of
them.
Sally, Bruce, Aras seem to have
a good system going.
>> Right there, Shane.
We're coming back.
>> PROBST: Terry, Austin and
Shane coming back with a big
load of coconuts.
That's not all of them.
They're going to have to make
another trip.
>> That's it!
>> PROBST: Bruce, Aras, Sally
have all their coconuts in one
load!
>> Turn around! You can pull!
>> PROBST: Shane, Austin, Terry
trying to unload, but they still
have more coconuts in their
boat.
Aras, Bruce, Sally have all
their coconuts in this net.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Terry, Austin and
Shane not giving up.
They don't have a lot of
coconuts left.
Remember, you've got to have
your tribe flag to finish.
>> Go get the tribe flag.
Go get the tribe flag, Sally!
>> PROBST: Sally forgot the
flag, had to go back and get it.
That's given time to Shane,
Austin, and Terry.
Bruce and Aras trying to unload
as fast as they can.
Sally has the tribe flag.
It's coming down to the wire.
The guys have to unload before
Sally makes it up the beach.
It's going to be close.
>> Let's go.
>> PROBST: Sally's got it.
Bruce, Aras, Sally win reward!
>> Yes! Good strategy, guys.
Way to play.
>> PROBST: Okay, Bruce, Aras,
Sally, tomorrow morning the boat
will pick you up, take you to a
nice little spot, breakfast in
bed.
Right now big decision to make.
Who are you going to send to
Exile Island?
You will choose one person from
each team.
>> From each team?
>> PROBST: All right, first
team, who's going to Exile
Island?
>> Austin.
>> PROBST: Austin.
First time there.
Cirie, Danielle, Courtney?
>> Danielle.
>> PROBST: Danielle is going to
Exile Island.
Boat's waiting for you.
You're heading out.
Bruce, Aras, and Sally, boat
will pick the three of you up
in the morning, take you to
breakfast in bed.
For the rest of you, I've got
nothing for you.
Head on back to camp.
(thunder rumbling)
>> Winning the reward challenge
is the greatest thing in the
whole wide world.
I get to have breakfast in bed
with Bruce and Aras, which is
going to be really interesting.
>> I'm getting irritable right
now.
Where is the boat?
I wake up like a kid on
Christmas.
I woke up so early, but we're
waiting for this boat and it's
just not coming.
It's raining out.
Like, there is no boat and I'm
just getting pretty anxious.
>> Ship ahoy, man.
Say it.
Ship ahoy.
>> There's no ship.
>> The moment I won it I
realized what I'd done.
I not only exposed a little bit
of my athleticism, but a lot of
my wit.
So the reward challenge did put
a target on my back.
I won the battle in spite of
the war, maybe.
>> Is that us?
>> Excellent.
>> Brucey.
>> Sally.
>> Oh, that's a nice sized boat.
>> Yeah.
>> Awesome.
>> Whoo!
>> Bye.
Enjoy the bacon and the eggs.
>> Aras, Bruce and I get in
this boat and we're just like
huddled in the front, like,
drenched, having no idea where
we're going, having no idea
what to expect.
And it's like this sandbar in
the middle of nowhere with this
beautiful canopy bed and it's
pouring rain.
And I'm, like, there is no way
that that is our reward.
I was so frustrated.
>> Oh, the whole bed is wet.
>> Gosh, that sucks!
The sheets are wet; the blankets
are wet; I mean, we're drenched;
we're cold.
>> Good morning.
Are you ready for breakfast?
>> Yeah.
>> Just relax, we'll bring you
breakfast in bed.
>> Oh.
>> Enjoy.
>> All of a sudden this tray is
set down and, I'm not kidding
you, it went from, like, this
cold miserable moment to the
most incredible day ever.
>> This is coffee.
>> It was kind of bittersweet
'cause two of our friends had
to go to Exile Island, but I
thought there was a meal fit
for a king and royalty.
Orange juice, sweet rolls,
fresh toast, butter and jelly
and hot pressed coffee with
cream and sugar, and the bacon
was out of this world.
>> Fruit?
>> Oh, look at those
raspberries!
>> We just devoured it.
It was every man for himself.
>> That croissant put me over
the edge.
>> Champagne.
>> Oh!
>> To the victors.
>> I never thought I could be
cold and wet and in a bed with
two strange men and feel so
comfortable.
It was the best meal I've ever
had.
>> Oh, I meant to ask Aras why
he picked Danielle over
Courtney.
Do you think he thought Danielle
could handle herself a little
better than Courtney out there?
My strategy is to try to coax
out of those guys who do they
think is going to be in the
final four and with that, it
puts two of their players kind
of out there.
>> What are your odds on the
final four, man?
What do you think?
You, Aras, Cirie and... tough
choice between Courtney and
Danielle.
>> I think we should put $20 on
it, Shane.
I found out some very important
stuff.
Two of their players, Danielle
and Bruce, are the next on the
pecking order, and if I can get
those guys over to our side,
this will totally swing the
game.
>> Oh, they are back.
They got bacon with them?
I try not to think about the
breakfast because I don't want
to hate them any more than I do
right now.
(laughs)
>> Toast, yeah, toast with
butter and jam.
>> And then we had to listen to
the stories of chocolate
croissants and sausages.
>> I had some of Sally's bacon.
I couldn't eat any...
I was dizzy.
(laughing)
>> Look at my stomach.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Rub it for luck.
>> I don't care how big your
stomach was.
That kind of pissed me off.
We're starving eating beans and
you're going, "Look, I'm so
full."
>> That's a belly!
I know.
>> I have to win something or I
will die in Panama.
(thunder rumbling)
>> This sucks so bad.
This is unbelievable.
Absolutely unbelievable.
It never stops.
(thunder rumbling)
>> Exile is just miserable.
Ever since yesterday it's not
stopped raining.
It's cold as hell.
This is the most miserable I've
ever been in my life.
>> This is putting up a strong
fight to be the worst day here.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> And don't get me wrong:
every day here sucked.
>> Everything's wet.
You can't even build a fire.
Austin and I have been hiding
under a tree, but we're still
getting soaked and it's just
miserable.
>> Being on Exile Island under
the torrential rains forced me
to go into the quickest bonding
experience I've ever been
through.
Luckily, Danielle and I got
along great and she stood
strong and I was proud of her.
>> Out of all of the people
that I had to get stuck on the
island, I'm glad it was Austin.
I know him a little bit more
personally and I have a little
bit more trust built with him.
God forbid something did change,
then, yeah, I am thinking
logically that Austin would be,
you know, a backup plan.
>> We're now down to three
ex-La Mina members, and at this
point, there don't seem to be
any chinks in the armor right
now with Casaya.
They don't like us; they don't
want us here; they're just
waiting to pick us off and
you're going "What can I
possibly do to change this?"
What happens if Austin and
Danielle found it?
Who gets it?
>> I have it.
>> Are you serious?
>> I am serious as a heart
attack.
I found it in 20 minutes.
>> Shut up.
>> No.
I have it.
I've always had it.
I had it from the first
frickin' day, 20 minutes later.
>> Terry has the individual
immunity idol from Exile Island
and I just about pooped my
pants.
I dug holes out there, so I
could just smack him, but I'm
so thrilled to hear that.
Holy ..., Terry.
God, this is a great day.
I love it.
I mean, the whole game changes.
That's a huge ace in the hole,
and I'm so excited for the next
immunity challenge because if
Terry wins, he could slip either
Austin or I the idol and I'm
home.
I'm absolutely thrilled.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Danielle and
Austin returning from Exile
Island.
(applause)
>> That was no vacation, buddy.
>> PROBST: You guys look
exhausted.
>> Worst experience of my whole
life.
>> That goes down in my book.
>> PROBST: What was the worst
part?
>> It did not stop raining.
Couldn't get a fire started
'cause everything was just wet.
>> I mean, we, the whole time,
feared hypothermia.
It was, it was miserable.
>> PROBST: And now you got to
take part in an immunity
challenge.
>> It's unbelievable.
>> PROBST: Let's get to it.
First things first. Terry?
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
you will race through a series
of Survivor obstacles.
It will work in four stages.
Here's how it goes.
For the first stage, all nine of
you must race to dig through the
sand and pull yourself under a
wooden fence.
The first six to finish move on
to the next round.
For the second phase, you must
complete a brain teaser.
Four written clues will guide
you.
As soon as you're done with the
brain teaser, you'll go up a
sand hill, through the maze,
over a second sand hill.
First three to finish this phase
move on.
For the third phase, you will
navigate your way across a rope
bridge using two wooden planks.
Once you reach the end of the
bridge, jump off the platform
into the water, climb up a steep
sand bank.
First two to finish move on to
the final round.
For the final round, you will
race through a series of
vertical, horizontal tunnels and
towers.
First person to finish wins
immunity; guaranteed a
one-in-eight shot at a million
bucks.
For the losers? Tribal Council.
Somebody will be voted out.
You will become the first member
of our jury.
The stakes are getting big.
Everybody ready?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Take a spot.
We'll get started.
Here we go, first round.
Six people moving on.
Survivors ready. Go!
Dig through the sand, pull
yourself under the fence.
Aras digging, Courtney making
good progress.
Aras is first through.
He's stuck!
He's got to dig a little bit
more of a hole for his butt.
Courtney coming through.
Courtney's stuck.
Aras still struggling.
Scraping skin off.
Shane trying to get through.
Sally moving through.
Sally's across.
Austin nowhere close.
Danielle's now through.
Four more people moving on.
Courtney's through.
Terry's through.
Two spots left.
Shane is stuck.
Gotta get through to get on to
win immunity.
Cirie is falling out of it.
Bruce still fighting, Austin
still fighting.
Who wants it?
Aras was the first one through
the fence and he's still stuck.
Shane moving on to the next
phase.
One spot left.
Austin moving on!
Second phase.
Sally, Shane, Danielle,
Courtney, Terry and Austin.
First three to finish move on to
the next round.
Survivors ready.
Go.
It's a brain teaser.
Read the clues, move the rocks
accordingly.
The green rock is in the same
column as the black and the blue
rocks.
The yellow rock is to the left
of the green and directly above
the orange rock.
Austin thinks he's got it.
Austin has it right. Move on.
The white rock is to the right
of the red.
Sally has it right. Move on.
Only three people moving on.
Yes! Go! Terry through.
Danielle through.
Austin and Sally with a little
bit of a lead.
Courtney has it right. Move on.
Shane, move on.
Austin really hustling.
Sally moving through.
Terry right behind making up
some time.
Danielle not giving up.
Shane hustling to get back in
it.
Courtney's quickly falling out
of it.
Austin with a big lead now.
First three through move on.
Austin's through.
Two spots left.
Terry fighting to stay in this.
Danielle falling out of it.
Sally's through.
Shane not giving up.
Terry, Sally, Austin.
All three ex-La Mina members
moving on to the next round.
Here we go. First two to finish
move on to the final round.
Survivors ready. Go!
Gotta use the planks to get
across the bridge one plank at
a time.
Balance, coordination, patience.
Manage all that with immunity on
the line.
Sally with a bit of a lead.
Terry right in there.
Austin-- two days on Exile
Island taking their toll.
Terry and Sally neck-and-neck.
Two people moving on.
Once you reach the top of the
platform, jump in the water,
climb over the sandy hill.
Terry and Sally neck-and-neck.
Austin not giving up, but
falling behind.
Terry at the end.
Sally, the first one on the
platform.
Terry on. Both in the water.
Terry moving on.
Sally moving on.
Austin out of it.
It is down to Sally and Terry.
For immunity, Survivors ready.
Go!
Terry dives through, Sally
crawling through.
Terry makes it through the
crisscross first.
Got a bit of a lead on Sally who
has to wait.
Pretty even.
Terry drops down.
Sally takes her time dropping
down.
She's losing some time.
Terry with a bit of a lead.
Sally's gonna have to catch up.
Terry up and over.
Crawling down now on his belly,
raking across it.
Sally gonna have to make up some
time right now.
Terry starting to dig.
Sally's gonna have to dig
quickly.
First person to the mat wins
immunity.
Guaranteed safe at Tribal
Council.
It's neck-and-neck!
Terry's through.
Sally's through.
Terry wins immunity!
Terry, come on over.
Once again, immunity is yours.
You're safe tonight at Tribal
Council.
For the rest of you, after 21
tough days, this game will come
to an end tonight for one of
you.
Grab your stuff. Head on back.
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> I'm so happy to be back here.
You guys have no idea.
When Aras chose me to go to
Exile Island, I was so mad.
It was an awful feeling and one
of the most miserable
experiences of my entire life.
Like, if you saw what pain and
agony we were both in, you guys
would be...
We really are.
>> That was fine.
>> Going into the challenge
today, I knew immunity was
vital because my back is
completely against the wall.
So when shocker of all shockers,
Terry comes through with yet
another win, I realize that
that was probably the end of
the game for me.
>> Good job, man.
>> Thanks.
Winning the immunity necklace
again keeps me out of hot water.
Kinda puts me in a place where
I can use the hidden immunity
idol as a big hunk of bait.
>> I mean, we developed a huge
respect.
>> Does she want to get to the
final five...
Yeah, I have it, and I want to
strategically put it on the line
so we, us three, keep going.
If Bruce and Danielle will come
over to our side, we'll have the
numbers.
And to lure Danielle over, I
will give her the immunity idol.
We'll give it to her, but first
I got to ask Bruce if she comes
over, will you come over
tonight?
And if that's the case, if it
all works out, then we're going
to the final five.
>> Have I ever told you how big
of stud you are?
>> Isn't he just sick?
>> In a major twist of fate, I
found out that my man Terry
found the immunity idol.
And now we haves us some
bargaining chips.
They're concocting their plan.
You're not part of it, Bruce.
>> Terry comes over to me
and he said he found out that
I'm at the bottom of the Casaya
pecking order and I'm gonna be
the first to go and Danielle
second.
You're at sixth place with them.
Your only chance is with us.
>> I like Terry. I admire him.
Terry and I have respect for
each other.
And if I'm at the bottom of the
pecking order, then Casaya tribe
broke their trust.
And so everything's up for
grabs.
>> What?
>> Yes.
>> No way.
No way.
>> ...so you don't have to worry
about it.
We wanted to play it safe.
We get back from the challenge
and we need to talk: who are we
gonna vote for?
And in my head I had already
thought it out 'cause I'm
assuming that if anybody has the
immunity idol, it's Terry.
>> That's crazy.
You think Terry wants to give
his idol to us?
It's an individual game right
now.
He needs that in his back
pocket.
Even if he does have it, which
he doesn't, he's not about to
give it away.
>> You're not listening to me.
Have you listened to me one
second?
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> Y'all chill, chill, chill.
Aras and Courtney, they got
into a big argument.
The problem is Terry already
has immunity.
And then say Terry has the
hidden immunity idol, he could
give that to anyone he wanted
to.
So say all of us vote for
Austin, and Austin pulls out the
idol, then the person with the
next-highest amount of votes,
which would probably be Aras,
will go home.
>> This is so stupid.
>> Would you hit me with just a
little bit of respect right now?
>> You treat me with a
little respect.
>> How am I not respecting you?
>> Wait, wait.
>> I haven't disrespected one
word and you're calling me
stupid?
>> Just relax.
>> Go over there and help Shane
with the fire and we'll talk.
Seriously.
Because look at you right now.
Go ahead, go with Shane right
now with the fire.
>> Did you see that?
>> Yeah.
>> For the first time ever,
Aras really, like, freaked me
out.
I think the boys just want to
cover their ass and they want
to get the girls off.
That's exactly why he was so
aggressive about it.
>> I've never seen him like
that.
>> He was, like, psycho.
The hidden immunity idol has
shaken things up.
I mean I want to stay loyal, but
if Austin does have the hidden
immunity idol, then if Aras
goes, well, I'm sorry but Aras
needs to be voted off at some
point.
>> Courtney has not displayed
one bit of intelligence since
she's been out here and it's
interesting that the two Casaya
guys are not being protected by
their tribe.
Either it's shortsightedness or
they don't mind losing one of
us.
>> Why?
>> I have been on Exile Island
for two days, I come back and,
bam, everybody's going crazy.
Austin and Terry said that I
was on the top of the line to
get knocked off.
And then Terry promised me that
he would give me the immunity
idol to get me to flop to be
with them.
It's tempting.
I don't know if I trust Aras.
So I have a lot of power.
The ball's in my hand.
I could actually transform this
game into a whole new thing and
maybe there's going to be
somebody different going home
than everybody thinks.
>> I do not agree.
>> We'll see what happens
>> Basically, we're playing a
shell game.
Where's the ball?
Under which shell?
And Casaya is divided on the
vote.
>> Great.
>> So I absolutely feel at risk
and I'm crossing my fingers and
just hoping that I don't get a
whammy.
>> PROBST: Hello, everybody.
>> Hey.
>> PROBST: Let's start with the
reward challenge.
Aras, it was clear even to me
that even though you and
Danielle were on separate
teams, you guys were working
together.
>> I feel like the team of men
had a bit of an advantage and
so I looked at my group and said
"Let's put all our coconuts in
the men's boat and hopefully,
we can get the women to do the
same," which would give us both
an equal shot at winning it.
>> Actually, it was really a
good plan for Aras because we
helped him stop the men and
helped him win.
Sorry, Aras.
>> PROBST: Aras, it's tough to
put yourself on a limb like
that because you expose
yourself.
>> It definitely weighs on my
mind, Jeff.
Coming here tonight I know that
if an immunity idol gets
played, I could easily be going
home tonight.
>> PROBST: So while Sally,
Bruce, and Aras are having
breakfast, Danielle and Austin
are in hell.
Austin, after those two days on
Exile Island, is it too soon to
say something like that builds
character?
Do you need time away from it?
>> When I look back upon my
entire Survivor experience,
even if I win a million
dollars, the first thing I'm
going to remember are those two
nights.
I have never had a more
character-building trying time
in my whole life.
>> PROBST: Danielle, when
you're in a situation like that
and you're with a stranger, do
all those things go away and do
suddenly the two of you just
bond together?
>> Absolutely.
I mean Austin and I got to know
each other so much better than I
did before we had that little
moment together.
It was a great bonding
experience and I'm just so
proud of myself that I came out
of there alive and I was
strong, and same with Austin.
>> PROBST: Change of topic.
Cirie, so how is this group
getting along now that you're
one tribe and the numbers are
whittling and the tension
starts to mount?
>> I think we get along fine
until Tribal Council.
When it's the day for Tribal
Council, you see La Mina here
and Casaya here and everyone's
basically scrambling.
>> PROBST: Courtney, does it go
through your head that somebody
in this group of six might be
looking ahead and thinking
there's a time for me to move
and it's before we get to six?
>> I think anyone that's
playing this game, if they're
playing it right, they're going
to be looking ahead.
And there's so many unknown
variables.
>> And again, the whole
immunity idol thing could pop
up at any time and one of us
could go home.
>> PROBST: Danielle, how do you
navigate knowing that as the
numbers dwindle, people are
going to realize "I'm on the
bottom and I've got to make a
move."
>> It's very difficult.
I go with my basic gut
instincts.
Whatever it tells me what I
feel is right inside, I mean,
that's the move that I make.
>> PROBST: Bruce, does it go
through your head, maybe I'm #6?
>> It's been going through my
head the entire time.
They could just be setting me
up for the fall.
Right now, I appreciate the six
I'm with.
But in the back of my mind, I
feel that I could be the first
to go.
>> PROBST: Shane, how much of
your time is spent thinking
about how tight is my six?
>> If someone flops now, it's
still five-four.
So two people now have to flop
from the six.
Which I would find...
it would be...
I would be stunned at one,
but it's impossible that two of
us would do it.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Terry has the individual
immunity necklace.
>> I'll be holding on to it.
>> PROBST: In addition, at this
point lots of people could have
found the hidden immunity idol.
If it comes into play, you'll
present it to me after the vote.
Whoever has it is immune and
the person with the next
highest numbers of votes is out.
It is time to vote.
Austin, you're up.
>> Best of luck to you, buddy.
>> You are my biggest threat.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Aras.
Aras.
Two votes Aras.
Austin.
Two votes Aras, one vote Austin.
Aras.
That's three votes Aras,
one vote Austin.
Austin.
Three votes Aras,
two votes Austin.
Austin.
That's three votes Austin,
three votes Aras.
Austin, that's four votes
Austin three votes Aras.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Exile Island, first
member of our jury: Austin.
That's enough votes.
Unless you have the immunity
idol, you need to bring me your
torch.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Austin, the tribe
has spoken.
>> Bye, guys.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
>> Later, man.
>> PROBST: Well, from this
point forward, the power in this
game begins to shift from those
of you still in the game to the
people on the jury.
You are now voting people out
that you need to vote for you
in order to win the million
dollars.
Just one of the things that
makes Survivor so much fun.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> What happens when I kick
your butts in the challenges?
>> PROBST: Terry's arrogance
irritates his tribe mates.
>> Maybe he'll break his arm or
something.
>> PROBST: A twist at the
immunity challenge divides the
confident from the concerned.
And Shane has a medical
question for the nurse.
>> I need you to look at this.
I have a chafing issue.
>> This was bar none
the hardest experience I've
ever gone through in my life.
It was very difficult for me to
negotiate the line between
integrity and playing the game
of Survivor.
I'm incredibly proud to have
made it to the jury. To my
whole La Mina tribe, you guys
were an absolute joy to be
around. Terry, you are
Terry, you are superhuman and