>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: Hiki finally sparked
a flame.
>> Guys, it's lit!
( laughter )
>> We got fire!
>> PROBST: On Raro...
>> Hey Adam, this is quite a bit
of work.
>> PROBST: ...priorities were
questioned.
>> Do you two want to a raised
platform?
>> I thought it sounded nice.
>> I know you do, but we have to
decide things as a group.
>> PROBST: At Aitu, Billy
wasn't pulling his weight...
>> If we lose Billy, we come
back stronger than ever.
>> PROBST: ...so Ozzy suggested
a bold plan to throw the
challenge and oust Billy.
>> Billy's just dead weight.
So we might as well cut our
losses now and get on with the
game.
>> PROBST: J.P. was on board,
but Cristina the cop was
skeptical.
>> I'm thinking, you know, this
doesn't seem right.
I don't know if I can trust
Oscar any more.
>> PROBST: But at the
challenge...
Puka's on the course, Raro's on
the course, Hiki's on the
course.
...Ozzy's plan went into
action.
Aitu completely unconcerned
about this challenge.
Puka, Raro, Hiki, all safe from
tribal council.
Aitu came in dead last and
chose Yul from the Puka tribe to
go to Exile Island.
>> Yul, boat's waiting for you
now.
>> PROBST: Before the tribes
parted, Billy thought he and
Candice made a connection.
On Exile Island, Yul deciphered
the clues and found the hidden
immunity idol.
>> Oh, mama.
I found the immunity idol.
If there's an opportunity
where it can change the game,
I'd use it.
>> PROBST: At Aitu's tribal
council, Billy revealed a
secret.
>> I fell in love in this game,
love at first sight.
Her name is Candice.
And in between...
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Candice from Raro
tribe?
>> Yeah, after the last
challenge, we sort of mouthed
the words "I love you" to one
another, and so that was my
prize.
My prize was her.
>> PROBST: In the end, Billy's
tribemates cut him loose.
Billy, the tribe has spoken.
18 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
( tribal-style singing )
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> I'm sorry, I can't get over
the love at first sight, I just
can't.
>> The what?
>> The love at first sight.
>> You know, anything's
possible.
Maybe he really had a crush on
her.
Maybe she was playing him
though.
I don't think she would have
said...
>> I think she was going...
>> You know what?
They never had any kind of,
like, contact or communication.
>> Study him, the way he is
around the camp, all that kind
of stuff, I don't know.
All the stuff that came out of
Billy's mouth tonight was
just ridiculous.
I don't even know... words
can't describe what... about the
Candice situation.
And if it's true, it's true.
But it's not true.
>> I was on the way.
Like we stop at this Vietnamese
restaurant because my wife and I
was hired by this restaurant
guy.
And this old man, he said, "I
come to United States, I'm so
lonely.
All my friends are in Vietnam."
He's, like, 50-something.
And he's just missing the old
days.
"But I come to United States
for my children's future."
I go, "How old are your
children?"
"Oh, 15 and 16."
( laughs )
15 and 16.
They tricked you, they tricked
you.
He goes, "What?"
15 and 16.
You think in a couple more
years they'll be in Iraq?
I'm sorry, for what?
( laughs )
You are Vietnamese.
You should know better about
war.
You should know all about war.
>> I have had sort of a coming
to Jesus in my own mind with
Cao Boi.
The guy just does not shut up.
>> What if they wanted to go to
college?
>> So what if you go to
If there is a draft, your ass
is going.
College.
Unless you're a senator's
children or congressman's
children, you're going.
Unless are you Mr. Bush's
children or your lineage is
blue or something.
>> I don't think he's all there.
I really in my heart of hearts
don't think he's all there, and
will ever be there.
Unless he's medicated.
>> "Your biggest challenge yet
will require brawn.
But if you're thinking wisely
it could be the winning tribe
you're on.
Use your powers of observation
and your intuition, too.
You may get a better life at
camp or just head home feeling
blue."
>> Just getting up, we got a
challenge early.
Morning challenge of some kind.
And the tribe is strong.
You know, we haven't lost yet.
We're one of the two tribes
that hasn't lost anything.
I went to Exile Island.
We came back and won the next
challenge.
That didn't really weaken us.
So we're okay.
And we're ready to rock 'n'
roll.
We're doing great.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Getting your first look at the
new Aitu tribe.
Billy voted out at the last
tribal council.
All right, we'll bring in Yul
from Exile Island.
( applause )
All right, first things first.
>> Retrieve the head.
>> PROBST: All right, drop your
buffs.
>> Take off our what?
>> Buffs.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: You have been living
together as tribes divided based
on ethnicity.
It is now time to integrate.
( laughter )
Women, all line up here on this
black line.
Men, over here on this black
line.
I want you to reach in and grab
a tile.
Don't look at it.
Keep it in your palm.
Different bag for the women.
All right, everybody put your
palm out.
Reveal.
Who's got the Xs?
Cecilia, Parvati, Brad,
Jonathan, you're the captains.
Take a spot on the black lines.
You're going to alternate
choosing tribe members.
The women will choose women.
The men will choose men.
Ladies, you're up.
Rock, paper, scissors to see
who picks first.
One, two, three.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Scissors cut paper.
Cecilia, you must select a
woman not from your tribe.
>> Pretty lady with the dreds.
>> Me?
>> PROBST: Say hello to Jessica.
>> You can call me Flicka.
>> PROBST: Parvati, you must now
select somebody not from your
tribe.
>> The cutie in the peach.
>> PROBST: The cutie in the pink
is Jenny.
>> Jenny.
>> PROBST: Jessica, you must
now select somebody not from
either of the two tribes.
>> The sister on the end.
>> PROBST: Sundra, join Cecilia
and Jessica.
Jenny, your choice.
Somebody not yet represented.
>> Camouflage.
>> PROBST: Cristina, joins
Parvati and Jenny.
Sundra?
>> Yellow.
>> PROBST: Becky, joins Cecilia,
Jessica and Sundra.
Cristina?
Rebecca joins Christina, Jenny
and Parvati.
Becky, everybody is represented
equally on both tribes.
Make your choice.
>> Candice.
>> PROBST: Candice rounds out
the five.
Rebecca, you're left with one
choice, your old tribemate,
Stephannie.
>> We got you, baby girl.
Come on home.
>> PROBST: Men, we're going to
do the same thing-- rock,
paper, scissors to see who goes
first.
On my count, one, two, three.
Scissor cuts paper.
Brad will pick first.
Brad, you're choosing a guy
that is not from your tribe.
>> J.P.
>> PROBST: J.P. joins Brad.
Jonathan, your choice, somebody
not from your tribe.
>> Yul.
>> PROBST: Yul, fresh from
exile.
The two guys that have been to
That will be interesting,
comparing notes.
J.P., your choice, somebody not
yet represented.
>> Nate.
>> PROBST: Nate, liking this.
Nate, J.P. and Brad.
Yul, you must now pick somebody
not yet represented on your
tribe.
>> I only have one choice then.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, from the Aitu
tribe, joins Jonathan and Yul.
Nate, you only have one choice.
>> Dude in the blue, then.
>> PROBST: Adam joins Nate,
J.P. and Brad.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, your choice has
been made for you.
Cao Boi joins Yul, his old
tribemate, and Jonathan and
Ozzy.
We are now divided into four
tribes, separated by men and
women.
All four captains, step forward.
Take an egg.
Hold it in your palm, face up.
That's yours.
When I tell you to, I want you
to squish them with everything
you've got.
Three, two, one, squish!
There are two new tribes.
Men with blue, join the women
with blue.
Women with red, join the men
with red.
>> Come here, sisters.
Hello!
( cheers )
>> PROBST: Ozzy, here's your
new buffs.
You are the new Aitu tribe.
You will live on Aitutaki beach.
Brad, you are the new Raro
tribe.
You will live on Rarotonga
beach.
All of the items accumulated
will be pooled together and
divided evenly between the two
tribes.
Two new tribes, a whole new
game.
Head on out.
>> A welcoming home...
>> Feast? That sounds great.
>> We just moved up, girl.
( laughter )
>> This a blessing from life.
Today is the best day ever.
( laughs )
It's like they took us out of
the ghetto and took us to Bel
Air.
We have been so weak and
depleted, and today we got to
throw off those stanky, yellow
buffs, and now we're a new
tribe.
>> How did you all feel when
you first realized how your
tribe was going to be set up?
What was y'all's thoughts,
feelings about that?
How you were segregated?
>> I thought it was weird.
>> You know what?
I thought it was okay just for
the fact that whether it's
good or bad, it brings a
attention to it and makes people
think.
I just think that's a good
thing.
>> The way our tribe is blended
at this point, it's all about
people and who we are and what
we bring to the table.
You really don't see color.
You see the heart of that
individual and what they're
doing to make your tribe
stronger.
And that's what this is all
about.
>> Adam's a snorer.
>> I don't snore.
( everyone talking at once )
>> We're back to America.
We're a melting pot.
I love it.
Everyone's all mixed back
together, and I just think it's
great.
>> First and foremost, it's
going to be all smiles and
"Pleasure to meet you" and
"Glad you're here."
But in the back of your mind,
it's a game, and you're in it
to win it for yourself.
And first and foremost: cold,
hard cash.
>> One, two, three!
( cheers and applause )
>> I'm so excited.
>> Welcome, welcome, welcome,
welcome.
( cheers and applause )
You're home!
Welcome.
>> First off, you guys did an
amazing job.
This is fantastic.
>> This is beautiful.
>> Is it watertight?
>> We have a wall.
Where's our wall?
Go back.
>> There's a wall in there.
>> We felt that Cecilia and
Ozzy were very welcoming.
They were just so excited.
Cecilia was the hostess.
She stood there and gave us the
spiel, point this out, point
that out, do that, do this,
this is what we got.
Mi casa es su casa.
They're Hispanic-- mi casa es
su casa.
That's beautiful.
We got our own little torch to
light up the whole place.
( laughter )
>> I'm definitely so happy
about the transition in this
game.
I definitely feel a change of
energy here.
I feel the vibration from other
people on my new tribe that I
didn't have the same in my old
tribe.
>> You're not Asian.
I love it.
I think you're fine, okay.
I think you're awesome.
>> I'm really excited about
just having fun people to hang
out with.
>> Okay, so I have to ask you
something.
Please don't be offended.
Billy, when he left-- and I'm
just curious-- Billy, when he
left, he said that you guys are,
like, love at first sight.
>> Love at first sight?
>> Yes.
And my jaw just dropped and I
was like...
>> You and Billy?
>> That is the weirdest thing I
ever heard.
So I got to ask you...
>> I mean, what did he mean by
that?
>> He said before the... we
left the last challenge, we
mouthed the words "I love you"
to each other.
>> No, he's...
>> Oh, no.
>> Were you saying good luck,
or...
>> No.
He said at the challenge or
whatever at the very end, he
just looked over to me and
Parvati, and he was like, "I'm
dead."
And I was like, "I'm sorry,
that really sucks" or whatever.
I was like, "We love you."
Like, our team, you know?
I didn't mean it like that.
>> He took it as you guys had a
love connection at first sight.
He said that that was his
million dollars, to get to be
with you.
Or like you know, know you,
like, be on the same team with
you.
>> You lead him on, Candice.
>> No, I did not.
( laughter )
>> You flirt, you.
>> You led him on.
>> Oh, please.
>> We've got to make a little
fire today.
Oh that's good.
Oh, that one's really good.
>> What are they doing?
>> I don't know, bonding.
( laughter )
>> We men.
>> There are so many men on
this tribe now.
It seems like we got all the
really big buff guys.
I'm absolutely going to flirt
with them.
Get them on my good side.
It's what I do best.
Aw, baby monkey.
>> Yeah, am I your baby monkey?
>> I already had Adam from the
beginning.
>> You have water in there?
>> I was drawn to Nate in the
first place just because he's
so, like, outgoing and funny and
kind of charming.
So I decided to work him, just
for starters.
Your pants are falling off,
Nate.
>> Lure him into my web, chomp
and suck his blood.
( laughs )
>> May have cooked these too
long, Cao Boi.
Cao Boi, how are you doing?
>> What?
>> I said how are you doing.
>> I'm doing fine, sir.
>> That's beautiful.
>> Cool.
>> I trust Yul, I trust Candice.
>> I totally agree.
No question that the four of
us should be...
>> Then we were thinking of
adding Flicka to make it five.
>> Believe me, I can get her
to do whatever we need her to
do.
>> Do you think...
>> I'll just say to her, "You,
me and Candice, we're going to
stay together and we're going
to deal with these other two
people, okay?"
>> I hear you.
>> I knew Becky was the person
I had to get to first.
But she was the key.
She came right to me.
She said, "Yul and I would like
to get together with you and
Candice."
I said, "Great."
I said, "I believe that I have
Flicka," hoping that she would
say "Okay, great."
>> I think we can align with a
couple of the Asians.
I think that's going to be able
to happen.
So we'll have a good, strong
five, I'm hoping.
All right?
But if anybody else approaches
you, just say, "Oh, yeah,
whatever," or "I'm not thinking
about it."
Just...
>> I'm not thinking about it.
I'm just sitting here.
>> I am thinking about it.
So you don't have to think about
it.
Let me think about it.
But I'm thinking about it.
Stay with me and Candice and
we'll take these other two and
the five of us will go to the
merge.
>> Jonathan wants me to stay in
the alliance from our original
tribe, in which I don't really
necessarily feel that
comfortable because I didn't
feel that comfortable in that
tribe to begin with.
>> We're strong.
We'll go all the way.
I mean, seriously, we'll make it
to the top five.
It's going to be cool, all
right?
>> All right.
I'm just kind of playing my
cards like I'm not really
thinking about alliances.
I'm just here to make friends
and see what happens and try
to, you know, go as long as I
can without feeling fake.
>> Candice and I, we were
talking and so she... her and
Jonathan basically were pretty
strong, too, and so, it's just,
you know, the perfect four.
But then we were trying to
figure out our fifth person.
So Jonathan mentioned Flicka,
and then we were deciding
between Ozzy and Cecilia.
So I don't know if her and Ozzy
already have an alliance or not
because they are two and they...
>> I'm sure that right now
they're kind of expanding a
little bit because they
realize that they're coming
into this with fewer numbers.
And so, I mean, if we went along
tribal lines, I mean, those
people would be voted out along
with Sundra.
I've to tell you something.
And again, you know, I'm
telling this because I totally
trust you.
>> Right, right.
>> This is sort of like my
gesture that, like, I trust
you and, like, all the stuff we
talked about, I really believe
in.
I found the idol.
>> That's so awesome.
>> Yeah.
>> First day or second day?
>> I found it... well, I found
it overnight just thinking
about the clues and kind of
working it out.
But you know, if we can somehow
turn the game around and get us
ahead, you know, you are in a
situation where I could save
your butt, I mean, I'll do it.
>> I appreciate it.
I trust you.
You know that I trust you.
>> Becky and I have, I think, a
tight bond and strong alliance
coming out of our Puka tribe.
You know, I think it's a huge
advantage in this game to have
somebody that you can absolutely
trust.
And I think, given our
backgrounds and our common
interests, I felt comfortable
disclosing the information to
her.
>> I am not going to tell
anybody.
I don't think you should tell
anybody again.
Oh, I'm so excited!
I'm so proud of you.
That's so awesome.
>> Oh, my God!
>> He has a what?
>> Octopus.
>> I felt like the man!
I was, "What, octopus, what do
you got now?"
It's a good feeling.
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
>> Pull it back.
Strong.
>> Look at him sucking me.
>> I told you.
( laughter )
>> He is going home!
>> Pull that head back.
>> Ha, ha.
>> Yeah, Nate.
>> How did you find him?
>> I don't think the guys or
anyone really expected me to do
it, to come back with
something, and something so
heavy.
Looking at it, you know, just
hanging, I was like, "Yeah,
we're eating this fool tonight."
>> We got dinner, ladies.
>> It's huge.
>> How did you get that?
>> I had a spear, and I
couldn't let go of the spear
because he would swim off with
it.
He was strong.
>> That is a lot of meat.
You need it.
You could probably eat that
whole thing yourself.
>> Probably.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's challenge, each tribe
will begin clipped together by a
rope.
In addition, each of you will
be carrying a 15-pound sandbag
on your back.
You will start on opposite
sides of the course.
On my go, you will race through
knee-deep water attempting to
catch the other tribe.
When you get tired, and some of
you will, it's okay to opt out
of the challenge.
But first, you have to take
your 15 pounds and give it to
another tribe member who is now
carrying twice as much weight.
First tribe to catch the other
tribe and tackle one of their
tribe members to the ground
wins immunity, is safe at least
one more day here in the Cook
Islands.
Losers, tribal council tonight,
somebody going home.
There is one more element to
this challenge.
The details are in the note.
It'll be revealed after the
challenge is over.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Get suited up, we'll
go.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors, ready!
Go!
This is an endurance challenge.
It is going to wear you out.
Water is almost knee-deep on
everybody.
Hard to walk through.
Both tribes have big guys at
the end.
Try to prevent easy tackles.
Both tribes have strong guys at
the front to make the tackles.
Aitu made up just a little
ground on that round.
Cecilia drops out, Sundra drops
out, Candice drops out, Becky
dropping out.
Aitu now down to five members.
Bold strategy move for Aitu.
All of their men now with 30
pounds.
Stephannie dropping out for
Raro.
>> PROBST: Cristina dropping out
for Raro.
Adam takes her weight.
Jenny dropping out for Raro.
Aitu still with a bit of a lead.
Jessica dropping out.
She's giving her weight to
Jonathan.
He's got three bags now, 45
pounds of sand.
Parvati dropping out for Raro.
Rebecca, the only woman left in
this challenge.
Aitu is down to four guys--
Ozzy, Jonathan, Cao Boi and Yul
shouldering a lot of weight.
Jonathan going to give 15
pounds to Ozzy.
Raro making up a lot of time,
starting to close in on Aitu.
Aitu has no options left.
Jonathan can hardly walk.
Cao Boi needs to be helped by
Yul.
Rebecca finally dropping out, a
key player in helping Raro get
a lead.
We are now even, four members
each.
J.P., Nate, Brad, Adam closing
the gap with each step.
>> Give it all you got.
Go, go!
>> PROBST: Raro making a go of
it.
J.P., Nate, Adam, Brad.
Yul going to try to fight them
off as long as he can.
But Cao Boi's too weak.
This challenge is over!
Raro wins immunity!
( cheers )
Raro, congratulations.
( cheers and applause )
Safe from the vote, guaranteed
at least one more day out here.
There is one more element to
this challenge.
I'll read the note.
"The winning tribe will choose
one member from the losing
tribe to go to Exile Island,"
which means the person you
choose to send to Exile Island
will miss tribal council
tonight.
You are keeping somebody in
this game.
A lot of ways to play this
strategically.
Figure out who it is going to
be.
Do you have your decision?
>> Candice.
>> PROBST: It was unanimous.
Candice, boat will pick you up,
have your stuff for you.
Head on out.
Okay, Raro, you guys are safe
from the vote.
Everybody's good.
Aitu, we have a date tonight at
tribal council.
One of the eight of you will be
going home.
You have the afternoon to
figure out who that's going to
be.
Head on back to camp.
>> Can we just take one second
and think of why they picked
Candice?
>> I don't think they would
perceive her as being the
strongest physically, so I
think they're just protecting
her.
>> They're trying to protect
her from us voting her off?
>> Candice went to Exile Island.
It has a huge effect on our
plans.
Prior to this, we had an
alliance going on between
myself, Jonathan, Becky,
Candice, and we were pretty
confident that with the four of
us pulling in one other person
we would have a numbers
advantage.
But now it doesn't look to be
the case.
And actually...
>> I need you guys, too.
We all need each other.
We just need to win.
>> But we have to obviously
write down some...
>> We have to let Becky go.
>> Okay.
>> I think Becky is the weak
link.
>> All right.
>> Cao Boi said alliance with
us, he said we're good, the
girls are good.
He said he really liked you,
you know, everybody...
We got all ( inaudible ).
I say we get rid of Becky.
Becky is seriously plotting.
>> All we need is five.
We are all voting for Becky.
Cao Boi, myself, Cecilia,
Sundra and Flicka seem to have
some sort of an agreement, and
we'll see if it stands.
>> Jonathan, what are you doing?
>> Let's...
Come here.
Let's...
I'll check in with you.
>> No more talking.
We're done.
>> I thought I had Flicka
handled.
I thought she was with me.
But she's not.
She's doing her own thing, and
I don't know how easy or hard
it's going to be to convince
her otherwise.
So we've got a serious problem
here.
Where do we stand right now?
It's you, me, Becky and that's
it.
We don't know where Sundra's
at.
We don't know where Cao Boi's
And Flicka is going to be
probably impossible to switch.
>> Really?
>> We're good, right, from what
we said.
>> Yeah, yeah, we need to stick
with it.
But Jonathan is just worried
because I'm not for sure saying
that I'm a part of their
alliance because I don't want
to be wishy washy.
>> You're just going to follow
your gut.
>> We just have to make it
through tonight.
We've got to get Flicka or Cao
Boi to vote for Cecilia.
And it's risky because if we
don't know that they are rock
solid going to vote our way,
then you and I put our necks way
out on the line.
Trying to convince Flicka and
Cao Boi to vote with us is the
key.
If not, then all bets are off
and it's going to be a whole
different kettle of fish.
All I'm concerned about is
making it to the merger.
Everybody you like is going to
get voted off.
>> I know, it's not about that,
though.
It's about having trust in the
people that you have a
connection with.
>> Okay, so I thought you and I
had a tight thing.
So we don't have such a tight
thing.
Do we not trust each other?
We're talking like adults.
>> I'm sorry.
We have to let Becky go in
total fairness.
She's the weak link.
Then we'll lose another one.
>> She's not a weak link.
>> She is.
She a princess out here.
You pay attention.
She's a princess out here.
I just watch and I just...
>> But she's not... she's not,
like, weak.
She's strong.
I think she has been very
strong and decisive on the
challenges.
I think if you look at Cecilia,
she hasn't been that strong.
She's good at puzzles, but
physically she hasn't been that
strong.
>> If five of us vote for
Cecilia tonight, okay, and three
of you vote for Becky, then all
of a sudden you're on the
outside and, boom, you're gone.
>> If we get rid of Cecilia,
we'll have our numbers, okay?
We can decide later on whether
we need to draw Becky, you,
Jonathan, Flicka.
That's five.
That's a solid five.
>> That's still not the point,
though.
>> Well, what is the point?
I guess we're talking apples
and oranges.
>> Yeah, we kind of are,
because I'm just thinking she's
the weaker link and I'm not
there.
>> I'm trying to think ahead of
that.
>> I'm not thinking ahead.
I'm not...
>> But this is a game.
This is like a chess game.
>> Yeah, right.
>> This is a 30 day...
we have 30 more days ahead of
us.
You can't just think about
tomorrow.
You have to put yourself in a
position that you can be there
in 30 days.
You have to think about that
now.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I mean, because otherwise
you won't be there.
>> Uh-huh.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I have to think about it still.
>> We've got to stick tight.
>> You present your point and,
okay, I'll listen to you.
>> I don't like the scheming of
man.
I really don't like that at all.
I feel like I've always been
blessed.
Maybe this time I'm wrong.
>> No matter what they said, I
said, "I'm going to talk to
Jessica first."
Okay.
>> I have a hard time
trusting...
>> I don't trust Jonathan.
>> He's manipulative.
>> I had a good talk with her.
She doesn't like the idea of
playing the game that way.
>> But Jonathan has a point, the
numbers game.
We have to make it to the
merger.
We can play the game some more.
>> I don't want to be picked
off.
>> I know, but they are playing
bad.
You are not part of the crowd.
I'm not part of the crowd,
period.
We're just stuck in this...
>> Now what do you do?
I don't know what to do.
I'm getting all wrapped up in
this whole drama.
I realize it's a numbers game,
but I have a lot of respect for
Ceci, so I don't know.
It's so hard.
I'm like, ahh!
>> Two ways to play the game:
"I like you, so I'm not going
to vote for you," or "Sorry, I
like you, but I got to vote for
you because I want to go
further."
We have two different
philosophies, and it's a war.
I don't know.
We'll see how convincing I've
been.
>> PROBST: Go ahead and have a
seat.
So let's talk about the merge.
Jonathan, in this case, the
tribes have been divided based
on ethnicity.
Did that add anything to the
merge?
>> I didn't think so.
Honestly, I didn't.
I think the captains selected
the strongest people they could
given the parameters.
We had a sense of who was
strong and I'm actually really
pleased with the way the merge
went.
>> PROBST: Sundra, as the only
person from one tribe, you
suddenly can become extremely
powerful as everybody now wants
your vote because you have no
allegiance to anyone.
>> Yeah, I mean, you could say
you are either vulnerable or
valuable, and I don't give
credit to either.
I just try to be there and
just use my gut to say, "Okay,
this is what I should do,"
because, as you know, there's
no way to guarantee the results
of playing this game.
>> PROBST: Yul, assess this
tribe.
What do you think would be the
best direction for this tribe
to head?
>> My sense is that some people
have different priorities in
terms of what they are looking
for out of being here.
I think some people are
strategizing and trying to make
alliances and came here to play
hard to win the game.
I think other people came here,
you know, hoping that this
is going to be a personally
fulfilling experience for
everyone.
>> PROBST: And Jonathan,
nothing wrong or right about
either one of those ends of the
continuum.
>> Absolutely.
Someone who's here to just
have the experience and not
play the game, they're going to
be playing the game.
The game is happening with them
in it.
And people who are here who are
strategizing, they're also
dealing with the personalities
here and they're really in the
experience.
And that's what makes it
interesting is that none of us
are thinking about it exactly
the same way.
Otherwise, it would be pretty
boring, I think.
>> PROBST: So Jessica, eight
days in, is this game already
more complicated than you
anticipated?
>> I think that I'm just not
used to the manipulation aspect
of it, and just where people's
intentions are gets really
confusing to me.
Like, are you really telling me
because you're being nice or
are you telling me this because
you're, like, trying to get me
on your side so you could,
like, get me to, like, vote
somebody off who I like, you
know?
It's just weird, because I'm
not ready to lose one of our
members of our tribe yet.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, how is this
tribe going to be different
after tonight's vote?
>> Well, I'm going to...
after tonight's vote, I'm going
to know where people actually
stand as to what they were
saying before.
So that's pretty much how it's
going to go.
>> PROBST: Before we get to the
vote, two of you have been to
Exile Island.
The hidden immunity idol might
have been found.
Just to be clear, here's how
it works: if the person in
possession of the idol receives
the highest number of votes,
you present that idol to me
after the vote, you're back in
the game.
And the person with the next
highest number of votes goes
home.
It is time to vote.
Yul, you're up.
>> Cecilia, I'm really sorry to
be sending you home.
And the vote was either going to
go against Becky or yourself.
And between the two, my loyalty
is to Becky.
Best of luck to you.
>> It's nothing personal.
I think you're amazing.
It's what I think will be
better for the tribe.
>> It's nothing personal, girl.
I'm just doing this as far as
strategy for moving the tribe
forward in this game.
>> You haven't made any effort
to try and connect to me, get
to know me at all.
>> You're a very classy lady.
This is nothing personal.
It's just strategy.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Cecilia.
Becky.
One vote Cecilia; one vote
Two votes Becky; one vote
Cecilia.
That's two votes Cecilia;
two votes Becky.
Cecilia.
We're three votes Cecilia; two
votes Becky.
Becky.
We're tied.
Three votes Becky; three
votes Cecilia.
Cecilia.
Four votes Cecilia; three
votes Becky.
One vote left.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Cook Islands:
Cecilia.
Please bring me your torch.
Cecilia, the tribe has spoken.
Well, one thing is clear, this
tribe is definitely not unified.
And only eight days in to a game
this unpredictable, certainly
risky.
Grab your torches.
Go back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: At Raro, new lines
are drawn.
>> The guys are just sitting
and the girls are working.
That just doesn't fly with me
at all.
>> PROBST: And at Aitu, Cao Boi
goes too far.
>> Oh, my God, a little chick.
Cao Boi is such a wild card.
I wouldn't trust him.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> This vote tonight, it's
insane.
It's just a testament as to
how quickly the game can change.
But I have no regrets.
I had a great time.
It was an amazing eight days.
I got to do crazy things that I
never thought I would ever do
and probably won't ever do
again.
I think that they made a mistake
voting me out.
I don't think this is going to
strengthen them.
It may weaken the tribe,
unfortunately.