>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, at Raro...
>> Kind of annoying that the
guys are just sitting and the
girls are working.
>> PROBST: ...the men were
secure with their position.
>> These girls are going to need
manpower, so the four-guy
alliance is definitely relaxed.
Nothing.
>> They're getting very
comfortable with their position
in this tribe, because they know
that we need them.
They're strong.
>> PROBST: Back at Aitu, Ozzy
brought in a big haul.
>> I'm happy being the sole
provider of this tribe.
If they lose me, then they're
going to be losing a lot of
strength.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Who will be the stronger
swimmer?
>> Go, Ozzy!
>> PROBST: ...it was Ozzy's
speed...
Ozzy first to the mast!
...and Cao Boi's magical spark
that made the difference.
Aitu wins immunity!
( cheering )
Raro, tribal council tonight.
Somebody from this tribe is
going home.
With tribal council looming,
Stephannie broke down...
>> PROBST: ...giving the men an
excuse to vote her out.
>> If someone doesn't want to be
here, I'm not going to keep you
here.
>> Can you put that log right on
top?
>> PROBST: But J.P.'s
bossiness...
>> Parvati, can you hand me the
machete?
>> PROBST: ...got the girls
thinking.
>> I would love to see us girls
align.
>> Why don't we switch this up
and just have all the girls
align right now?
>> Five women, four men.
So if we're going to do any type
of alliance, it needs to be done
right now.
>> PROBST: And at tribal
council...
Fourth person voted out of the
Cook Islands...
...the tribe blind-sided J.P...
>> Man, you guys outwitted me
big time.
>> PROBST: ...voting out one of
their strongest members.
J.P., the tribe has spoken.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I don't know.
>> You know?
Now the game kind of really
turns on, because the guys all
have to watch their backs, you
know, as a unit, because these
women could try to eat us off.
>> All right, I'm going to go
fish.
>> Are you?
>> I think so.
>> Let me finish brushing my
teeth.
>> We're outnumbered.
These women thinking they're so
tight and so headstrong.
>> You know, they think they can
run the world.
So I got to let them know,
"Yeah, you guys do need us."
>> No wood means no water.
No water means no life out here.
>> It's really funny.
The guys have really stepped it
up since J.P. is gone.
>> Unbelievable.
>> Nate did get a massive pile
of wood this morning.
I've never seen a pile of wood
bigger than that.
>> Good morning.
>> And Adam went and got, like,
five crabs.
>> Wow.
>> And Brad went out and just
went fishing.
They're just so much more manly
now that the top dog is gone.
I think they're definitely
trying to prove themselves to
the women so that the women
don't try to overthrow all the
guys.
I love it!
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Mine are worse, aren't they?
Are mine worse?
>> Yours aren't that bad.
>> I think my right one is
worse.
>> Really?
>> Well, so far we have Sundra,
we have Candice, and we have
Becky just sitting around.
That annoys me.
They don't even try.
>> Today is a good day to be
just relaxing, because...
>> I agree.
>> We will keep winning our
challenges, I hope, but if they
don't correct themselves, they
will be eliminated.
>> We have tree mail.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Yay!
>> "Today you'll compete two by
two.
How will you take the strain?
A chance at more food and a
whole lot more flavor for the
tribe with the last pair to
remain."
>> All right, this'll be good.
I like this.
>> We're going to be eating good
tonight.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Raro, come on in.
Getting your first look at the
new Raro Tribe.
J.P. voted out at the last
tribal council.
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: Guys ready to get to
today's reward challenge?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Here's how it works.
Each tribe will select three
pairs.
Each pair will stand on a
platform with each person using
one arm to hold on to a hook.
Every two minutes, members of
the opposing tribe will load up
one of those pairs with five-
pound weights.
The more weight you add, the
harder it will become to hold.
Last pair left standing wins for
their tribe reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Big reward: more
fishing supplies, spices, and
bottles of wine.
>> Whoa.
>> Ah.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will choose one
member from the losing tribe to
go to Exile Island.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Okay, we have our pairs.
For Aitu, Jonathan and Yul,
Sundra and Candice, Ozzy and
Jessica.
For Raro, it's Nate and Adam,
Rebecca and Stephannie, Cristina
and Brad.
The loaders for Aitu, Cao Boi
and Becky; for Raro, Parvati and
Jenny.
Let's begin.
Grab your weights.
Adam and Nate going to get some
weight, five pounds each.
Candice and Sundra getting five
pounds each.
Now we wait.
>> I hope they just pile up on
us, because we're just going to
hold it for as long as we
possibly can.
>> And you guys kill them out
there.
Let's get that wine.
>> PROBST: All right, let's add
some more weight.
Raro giving Jonathan and Yul
their first five pounds.
Nate and Adam getting another
five pounds from Aitu.
( Nate laughing )
Adam and Nate each with ten
pounds.
Yul and Jonathan, Candice and
Sundra all have five pounds.
And we wait a little more.
>> Wait a little more.
That's like a bad pun, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Oh.
Time to add more weight.
Aitu completely loading up on
one pair.
Raro, on the other hand, is
distributing it evenly among all
three pairs.
Adam, Nate, how is that feeling?
>> Feels like getting some wine
tonight and getting faded.
Wine tonight.
>> Whining.
>> PROBST: Ooh.
>> Hard-core.
You're asking for it.
>> PROBST: All right, here's
where we're at.
Adam and Nate, Jonathan and Yul
holding strong with 30 pounds
each.
At 15 pounds, we got Brad and
Cristina, Candice and Sundra.
With ten pounds each,
Ozzy/Jessica and
Rebecca/Stephannie.
>> They're struggling, you guys.
>> They're struggling.
Keep your eyes on them.
>> PROBST: Yul drops his bags.
Yul and Jonathan out of the
challenge.
Take a seat on the bench, the
first pair out.
Time to add more weight.
Rebecca and Stephannie taking it
for Raro.
Jessica and Ozzy with five more
for Aitu.
Aitu now down to two pairs and
Jessica struggling.
>> Come on, Aitu.
You guys are doing awesome.
>> PROBST: Nate and Adam still
holding strong with 30 pounds
each.
>> Handsome boys, make quite a
pair.
>> ♪ Ebony, ivory... ♪
>> PROBST: Getting heavier by
the minute.
Rebecca drops her weight.
Rebecca and Stephannie now out.
Raro loses their first pair.
Take a seat on the bench.
We are now even.
>> Hold it, hold it, baby.
You breathe in really hard and
do it once.
Squeeze that hand.
Don't drop it.
>> You can do it.
You can do it.
>> Don't drop it.
>> Pull it down.
Pull it down.
>> I can't.
>> Come on, come on.
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: Sundra drops her bag.
Candice disappointed.
Aitu has lost their second pair.
Everything now rests on Ozzy and
Jessica for Aitu.
Somebody from the losing tribe
going to Exile Island.
>> Come on, Cristina.
>> Hold it, baby.
>> Ooh, she's going to drop it.
I see her drop it.
>> I don't think so, girl.
>> She's not going to drop it.
>> She's going to drop it.
>> Mind over matter.
>> She's taunting you.
She's taunting you.
Yeah, she's a young one.
>> Power of the mind is a
dangerous place to wander.
She's going to drop it.
>> Whatever.
>> PROBST: Time to add more
weight.
Brad and Cristina with 20
pounds.
The only place to go for Aitu,
Jessica and Ozzy.
Big guns still holding on for
Raro with 30 pounds each.
Nate struggling to hold on.
>> You're doing good.
Don't give up.
>> PROBST: Adam very close to
losing his weight.
>> You got it, you got it.
Good job.
>> PROBST: Fights back.
>> That's what I'm talking
about.
>> Stay with it, Cristina.
>> I can't pull it down.
Ah!
>> PROBST: Jessica drops out.
Raro wins reward.
( Raro cheering )
Raro, congratulations.
Big reward.
In addition, you are choosing
one person from Aitu to go to
Exile Island.
Who's it going to be?
>> I think we should stick with
one of the three that have
already been there, Jonathan or
Candice or Yul.
>> I think Jonathan.
>> We're sending Jonathan back.
>> PROBST: Jonathan going back
to Exile Island.
Follow the path right there and
around the palm tree.
All right, Raro, come get your
reward.
>> Awesome.
( Raro cheering )
>> I slept like a baby.
>> Because of the wine?
>> Yeah, dog.
>> Hey, guys, a I got an octopus
stuck to my foot.
Look at this thing.
( laughter )
I stabbed it with a spear.
Get off me!
>> I got you.
I got you.
There.
>> That's like lunch and dinner.
>> Okay, we need to get... what
are we doing with that?
>> It needs coconut juice.
We need to have a bunch of
coconuts.
>> Okay, okay.
>> We need some coconut pieces
and then some salt water.
>> I think Cristina thinks she's
an asset because she cooks our
food.
But you know, it's not that hard
to throw together a coconut
stew.
>> And then we'll put the crabs
with the octopus.
And if it doesn't taste good,
don't tell me.
And we got to get that pot so we
can drink water.
Oh, you know what?
We need salt water in there.
Yeah, and then we need some more
salt water in that.
>> She tells people, points
things, "Can you do this?
Can you do that?"
>> Can you grab that?
After we cut up the octopus,
Cristina grabbed a pot full of
it, and I grabbed the knives and
the cutting boards to wash
those.
And I said, "Oh, I'm going back
up."
>> Somebody help!
Can one of you guys help?
I got the octopus out of the
pot.
>> The octopus spilled all over
the place.
>> I'm going to go assess the
damage.
>> I almost lost it all.
I thought Jenny was right here,
and I was trying to wash it, and
everything started falling out.
I'm like "Hello?"
>> We need to be careful with
it.
I mean...
>> I know, but I couldn't do it
myself, so...
>> I worked hard this morning to
get the octopus, and then
Cristina dropped the bucket, and
there were pieces of octopus now
all over the water.
So that really bothered me.
I don't know what she was
thinking.
They said they got it all back.
She said that she thought you
were there.
>> What?
>> I don't know... I don't
know... I don't know what's
going on.
>> Oh, come on.
>> She came with the pot.
I came with the knives and the
cutting board.
That's what I was cleaning off.
Adam goes, "She thought you"--
meaning me, I was right there
next to her.
And I'm thinking, "She going to
blame me for losing the
octopus?"
You don't need two people to
clean up octopus.
>> Yeah.
>> Cristina is coming across as
like our new J.P.
So she better watch herself.
>> Yul, do you want to go out
fishing?
>> I'd like to try to catching a
chicken.
>> Okay.
>> We're thinking about making
an expedition to go check out
the island over there.
We're starting to run out of
resources over here, so we're
going to go check it out.
>> Cao Boi, Ozzy, and Jessica
are setting up to go on an
expedition to explore out in the
lagoon.
It's going to take a lot of
energy to paddle out there and
paddle back.
So that's the reason I'm not
going.
You know, I think the three of
them, they're kind of sticking
together, they're trying to grab
somebody along with them to
vote.
>> Sundra, you want to come?
It would be four of us.
>> Cao Boi, Flicka, and Ozzy
wanted me to go with them, but I
wasn't trying to do that,
because being out there hours
with them alone, that was not
going to be fun.
Because I know that they want to
try to prod me more, and it gets
uncomfortable, and I'd rather
not be in that position.
>> I'm going to chop this one up
because I'm kind of hungry.
Right now we have our solid four
alliance: myself, Jonathan,
Becky, and Candice.
Cao Boi and Flicka voted with us
last tribal council, but it's
just hard to be in any kind of
strategic alliance with them
because you have no idea what's
going to happen on a day-to-day
basis.
You want to chat?
We need a fifth in order to have
the numbers.
>> What's going on?
>> Sundra, I think, is someone
that everyone is kind of leaning
towards because she seems not to
be a manipulative person.
She seems that if she were to
commit, that she would be very
dependable.
And you know, she's kind of out
here by herself, and I think
she's looking for a home.
We just want to lock down the
final five, a strong alliance.
We want to find the people who
aren't going to waiver.
>> I'm definitely... I'm
definitely down.
>> Okay.
>> I am down.
Have you spoken to Ozzy?
>> No.
>> No, I mean...
>> We're just trying to read
him.
>> I like you, all right?
And I think everyone else does
too.
And personally, I don't know, I
mean, Ozzy seems like an okay
guy, but I just... I don't trust
him.
I don't know why.
>> No, for sure.
>> We trust you.
>> If it definitely... you know,
if we have to, unfortunately,
go to council, I'm part of the
five.
>> Okay.
>> My position in the tribe, I
don't know, I mean, you know,
I've had people come and tell me
that they want me to be in their
alliance.
Of course that feels good.
I'm very happy that I got over
that hurdle of being the
outsider, and I genuinely feel
that I'm a part of this alliance
now.
But who knows?
I mean, that could change five
minutes from now.
I just have to see.
>> Yeah, we just found us a
different island.
We figured we should take a
little expedition, see what we
can get.
>> I'm excited.
It's like having a picnic.
>> A-ha.
This is gold.
Looking for the noni, because
we've got a lot of cuts, see?
That guy right there.
Just got cuts all over the
place, and noni's a really good
antiseptic, keeps us nice and
healthy.
We get some more coconuts, and
who knows what else we'll find
out here?
( laughter )
>> How you doing?
>> Why is this tribe coming our
way?
>> Why is their tribe here?
>> Yeah.
>> We are exploring, playing
around.
>> Are you going to welcome us
into your home or not?
>> Yeah, come in.
>> Okay, okay, well, we're
welcome, hey.
>> I'm like, "What the..."
>> I think this is meant to be.
I think is meant to be.
Booty man, how are you, my man?
>> What's up, my brother?
>> All of a sudden Ozzy, Cao
Boi, and Jessica walk up, which
was a huge shock.
>> Parvati.
>> You're Par...
>> Par...
>> Parvati.
>> Parvati, Parvati.
>> I didn't like it at all.
I don't think they should be on
our island.
This is our turf.
This is our territory.
They got their own island.
>> Oh, man, look at that.
They got knives.
They got whetting stones.
>> It was like awkward silence,
crickets chirping.
Then Cao Boi launches into this
huge, like, speech about Chinese
symbology or something.
>> In our culture, we the revere
the dog, the horse, the turtle,
and the dragon.
Those are the four creatures
that we revere, okay?
Every time, if you look at your
life, you'll you find a lot of
dragons and monkeys and rat
friends.
If you guys are dragons or rats
and monkeys, you find a lot of
your...
That's the dog.
The second one is the horse.
So in wartime, the horse help
the soldier defend the nation.
In peacetime, it helps with
transportation.
Giant turtle, as big as this
whole area, giant.
>> After a while of just
listening to him talk over and
over and over and over again, it
was a little bit much.
And we were kind of like all
looking around at each other
like "Okay, is he going to stop
talking?"
>> We want to harvest some noni
if you guys don't mind.
We don't have any noni.
People are hurting all over.
>> I love it.
>> You guys want to work
together to get some coconuts?
We'll split with you.
>> It won't give us energy.
It'll just taste better.
Okay, that's true.
Okay, I'm asking for too much.
>> Let's get out of here.
>> All right, thank you.
>> Bye.
>> Thanks, everybody.
>> It's very primal out here.
So when the other tribe comes
and invades that, I don't like
that at all.
>> "To find what you seek, a
charm of great worth, get in the
right spot and look deep in the
earth."
I was in shock that they picked
me to come back to Exile.
I thought it was stupid for them
to send me if the idol hasn't
been found, because I'm sure as
hell going to try to find it.
Just like playing in a big
sandbox, a million-dollar
sandbox.
I dug for hours, and you could
bury Yao Ming in that trench.
And there was no idol there.
At this point, I have to assume
the idol has been found.
Otherwise, I'm a complete moron.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Jonathan
returning from Exile Island.
( applause )
>> How are you guys doing?
>> All right, Jonathan.
Come on over.
>> PROBST: So, Jonathan, did you
spend some time looking for the
idol?
>> A lot of time.
Dug a big hole.
>> PROBST: Are the clues at a
point now where you think you
know where it should be?
>> I think I know where it was,
but it ain't there now.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's immunity
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First thing's first.
Cao Boi, take back immunity.
Once again immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you are
going to race to assemble
stepping poles.
You will then use those poles to
transfer two tribe members from
one large platform to another
platform.
All eight tribe members will
then swim out to one final, very
small tower.
First tribe to get all eight
tribe members to the top of the
tower with both feet on or above
the top deck wins immunity.
Losers, tribal council, somebody
going home.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready.
Go!
Got to build your stepping poles
first.
Once you have the poles you want
to use, head on out to the water
and start walking.
Aitu making good progress on the
poles.
Nate thinks he's got it figured
out.
>> That's good.
That's it.
>> PROBST: Aitu has a good
system.
Raro falling behind.
Aitu has all three poles put
together.
They're in the water first.
Raro in the water with their
three poles.
>> Jenny, get up there.
>> Get up there, Jenny.
>> Get up there.
>> PROBST: Jenny first on the
pole for Raro.
Aitu's lead is gone as their
poles fell apart.
Jenny on to the second pole.
>> Take it one girl at a time,
guys.
>> PROBST: Jessica using a very
different strategy, standing
straight up, trying to balance.
Jenny swatting, kneeling,
lowering her center of gravity.
Jenny almost loses it, regains
her balance.
Aitu only using two poles,
trying a different strategy.
Raro with a bit of a lead.
We're still early in this
challenge.
>> Ah!
>> I got it, I got it, I got it.
>> PROBST: Jessica really
struggling to hang on.
Nice recovery.
Fall off now, you will lose a
lot of time.
Raro now drops their third pole.
They're now using two poles.
>> Go!
>> Jump!
>> PROBST: Jenny on to the first
platform.
Raro heads back to get Parvati.
Jessica close enough to jump.
>> One more.
>> PROBST: Can't do it.
Raro now with the lead.
Parvati on the pole.
Jessica across for Aitu.
Parvati now on her second pole.
Aitu's going to have to make up
ground.
>> We're going to have to go
farther than before, guys.
>> Take your time.
Take your time.
>> PROBST: Parvati inches her
way on to the next pole.
Aitu trying to take bigger steps
to make up some ground.
Aitu has made up a lot of
ground, but Raro still with the
lead.
>> You got it?
>> PROBST: Parvati getting
closer and closer to the second
platform.
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
>> One more.
>> PROBST: Very close.
Raro has both people on the
platform!
Everybody got to climb to the
top.
Everybody up!
Go!
Raro into the water, heading to
the final tower!
Aitu got to get up the tower!
Get up that tower and off!
Get up, Sundra!
Go, go, go!
Aitu in the water!
Got to get all eight tribe
members on or above the deck.
It's very close.
Cao Boi falls off for Aitu.
Raro, the entire tribe falls
off, got to try again.
>> Get on back.
>> PROBST: All eight members
must have their feet and their
body on or above the top deck.
Aitu now in the lead.
Going to have to work together,
get everybody above the deck.
Immunity on the line, tribal
council tonight.
>> Get one foot on.
Come on, baby, get foot on
there.
>> PROBST: Aitu very close, only
two feet away.
Aitu wins immunity!
( Aitu cheering )
>> Damn!
Aitu, congratulations.
( applause )
>> Tanga, Tanga, Tangaroa,
Tangaroa.
>> PROBST: Aitu safe from tribal
council, nobody going home.
Raro Tribe is down to eight.
Tonight it will move down to
seven.
For one person, this game is
about to end.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Good job, you guys, anyway.
>> I think we did well.
>> We did do well.
>> Okay.
>> All right?
Everyone's cool?
>> We just came back from losing
our challenge, and now we're
faced with another tribal
council.
A few of us were around the
fire, and it was a unanimous
agreement to get rid of Cristina
today.
>> Good job.
That at least got three.
>> We're all annoyed by Cristina
and how she talks a big game,
yet she doesn't really perform
as well around the camp.
>> Are you cool with that move
that they're calling?
>> What else would it be?
It'd either have to be me or
her.
>> No, it ain't you, mama.
>> I could easily see myself
going home and getting some
mashed potatoes and gravy.
>> What are you saying?
>> I said I could easily see
myself getting some mashed
potatoes and gravy.
>> You've come too long, mama.
Stephannie kind of said how she
really just wanted to get some
mashed potatoes, you know, just
kind of like that hint of like
"You know, I'm kind of done with
the game."
I was like "Damn, this girl's
done."
You know, the other day she made
that comment, saying, "Vote me
off, guys.
You know, I feel like I'm the
weakest link."
But that was just icing for the
cake today.
>> Yeah.
>> And I was like yeah, yeah.
Stephannie kind of gave me
this... Stephannie kind of gave
me this vibe like "Are you
sure?"
And then she's like, "Part of me
can see myself having some
mashed potatoes later."
>> She's done.
She's knows it.
>> She's already mentally
checked out.
She told Nate that... she's like
"Part of me could really use
some mashed potatoes tonight."
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah.
And if someone says that, to me
that just means you're gone.
>> You're done.
>> I think that Stephannie has
mentally checked out.
>> Really?
I think the other girls have...
>> Decided on Cristina?
>> I'm going to think about it.
>> Yeah, keep it in the back of
your mind.
>> Do you want to stay in the
game?
>> Yeah, I want to stay in the
game.
>> Because I don't know.
Some people are saying that you
are saying... making comments
that you want to go, like you
want to go home and, you know,
eat mashed potatoes or
something.
>> It's amazing how one little
thing can just be taken out of
context, you know?
>> Everyone's trying to watch
their own back right now.
If you slip up and say
something, they're going to use
that, and they're going to
extort it and use it to their
advantage.
You have to really watch
yourself.
>> Wow.
Me requesting mashed potatoes
and gravy became table topic for
everybody else at the camp.
I was like, "You know what?
I just may as well just keep my
mouth shut."
I said I was just, you know,
having fun, you know?
I didn't expect him to take that
and turn it into some big deal.
Yes, I'd like to be here.
But if my efforts working for
this tribe doesn't show that I
want to be here, I'm not going
to beg anyone.
I don't do that.
>> I just talked to her.
She says she still wants to be
in the game.
>> That's what she told me
earlier today too.
>> I think Stephannie tends to
be some dead weight on our
challenges.
>> You think she's weaker than
Cristina?
>> I think they're both pretty
bad.
>> Cristina annoys the hell out
of me.
>> She annoys the... everything
she does.
>> Me too.
>> I'm like... argh!
The only reason I switched is
because Nate said that she was
talking about going home and
getting some mashed potatoes or
something like that.
>> No.
I don't think she said that.
>> She doesn't want to go.
>> I don't think she wants to
go.
I'm voting my conscience.
>> PROBST: Adam, at challenges,
this tribe is not doing very
well.
You're back to tribal council
for the second time in a row.
>> I understand that, Jeff.
We are improving, though.
Our communication's getting
better.
You know, we were dominating
today, and it was just there at
the end.
But I'm proud of us, and we'll
be all right.
Don't worry about us.
>> PROBST: Brad, who do you get
along with best out of this
group?
>> I get along with pretty much
everyone.
And I wish could say, "Oh, I
don't like this person," or,
"This person really rubs me the
wrong way."
That's not the case.
That really isn't the case.
I get along with everyone pretty
much evenly.
>> PROBST: Steph, where do you
think you fit in the group if I
were to ask all these other
people?
>> I really haven't formed any
close-knit bonds with anyone.
I'm kind of friendly with
everyone.
I bring that nice presence.
And when I'm needed, I'm there.
When I'm not needed, I'm not
there.
Just that simple.
>> PROBST: Nate, last tribal
council, you voted out J.P., who
was deemed "bossy."
So is there much more harmony
now that J.P.'s gone, or did
somebody else step up and is now
the new bossy person?
>> I think the tribe can feel
that sometimes Cristina can be a
little overpowering, a little
overbearing.
It's kind of her attitude, and
it's powerful and dominant, and
being told what to do sometimes
rubs people the wrong way.
>> PROBST: Cristina, a big batch
of brutal honesty.
>> You know, I never realized I
was like that.
Maybe because I'm out of my
environment, and I'm usually
around other police officers.
You know, I didn't mean to
offend anybody.
I mean, I'm glad you guys told
me about it, and it's over with.
If I offended you guys in any
way, I'm glad you guys told me,
and I can take care of that.
>> PROBST: Adam, do you think
this tribe, to date, has been
honest with each other?
>> I think we're honest.
You know, I thought Cristina
knew she was kind of like that
way.
You know, it's just her
personality.
And you know, it can be a little
nerve-racking sometimes.
>> PROBST: Rebecca, do you think
this tribe should be more candid
with each other?
>> Honestly, I'll know better
after tonight, because this was
the most honest thing that came
out of council.
And when we go back to camp,
I'll see how it goes.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
If somebody has the hidden
immunity idol, and it turns out
you need to play it tonight, you
would play it after the vote.
You would then be safe, and the
person with the next highest
number of votes would go home.
It is time to vote.
Brad, you're up.
>> Stephannie, I'm sorry.
I think are you a great person.
God bless.
>> Just because, sweety, just
because, nothing personal.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Cristina.
Stephannie.
Two votes Stephannie, one vote
Cristina.
Stephannie.
That's three votes Stephannie,
one vote Cristina.
Stephannie.
Four votes Stephannie, one vote
Cristina.
Fifth person voted out of the
Cook Islands, Stephannie.
That's five, that's enough.
Unless you have the hidden idol,
you need to bring me your torch.
Stephannie, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Maybe tonight will
change things, point this tribe
in a new direction.
We'll see.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> You said I annoyed you.
>> It's your personality.
>> You could have said something
to me.
I never thought that's what they
thought of me.
>> People were coming into this
village, and they were
kidnapping people.
I had this dream.
I was dealing with all these
supernatural people.
And I woke up, and I go, "Whoa,
this is how you can defeat the
immunity idol."
>> PROBST: Win or lose, both
tribes will vote somebody out.
>> Ooh!
>> I would have loved to have
stayed in the game a little
while longer.
But if your mind's not
completely there 100%, then your
tribe is going to feel that.
And you don't want to be a weak
link to your tribe.
I had wonderful tribe mates.
I was thankful to have been a
part of the experience, and I
wouldn't trade it for the world.
Thanks.