>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> It pissed everyone in this
game off.
>> PROBST: Jonathan felt the
backlash of betraying his former
Raro tribe and joining the Aitu
four.
>> It's vile to me.
I think that he's a filthy,
miserable rat.
>> PROBST: At the reward
auction...
Sold to Jonathan.
...Jonathan's behavior...
>> And no sharing, right?
>> PROBST: ...fueled resentment.
( burps )
And Yul revealed a powerful
secret.
>> I have it.
>> PROBST: The immunity idol.
>> It's a compass on the
necklace.
>> PROBST: Back at camp...
( burps )
>> Oh, I definitely smell that
pepperoni.
>> PROBST: ...Jonathan's
character was questioned, even
by his new allies.
>> He's obnoxious.
>> Jonathan was a little too
arrogant, and it just shows a
little bit maybe of what his
true character is like.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Adam is the first to start
untying.
...Adam, Jonathan, and Parvati
fought for survival.
Adam has the key-- he's moving
on!
But it was Adam who came out on
top.
Adam wins immunity!
Adam, safe from the vote
tonight.
Back at camp...
>> Are they eating?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Candice
had it out.
>> Since when do you guys not
share?
>> Didn't you call me a
disgusting rat?
>> Well, Jonathan, you're a rat
because you betrayed everybody
in this game.
>> Jonathan is just a slimeball
and needs to be voted off.
>> PROBST: Knowing they were
outnumbered, Adam, Parvati, and
Candice put pressure on Yul to
dump Jonathan from the Aitu
alliance.
>> Candice, Parvati, and Adam
threatened me, pointing out the
fact that they would be on the
jury and if I didn't vote off
Jonathan they would hold me
responsible, and I'm honestly
concerned about it.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
>> What am I?
>> PROBST: ...things heated up.
>> You're a rat.
>> That's a fact, that I'm a
rat?
That's enough out of you.
>> There's absolutely no reason
for you to be around now,
though.
>> Says you, Jack.
>> PROBST: But in the end, Yul
stuck by Jonathan.
13th person voted out and the
fifth member of our jury.
Candice was voted out and gave
Adam one final good-bye.
Candice, the tribe has spoken.
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I expected no less.
So it was all fine.
Wow, what didn't happen at
tribal tonight?
It got pretty crazy there.
I was called all kinds of names.
"Rat" and "cancer" were the two
that I remember the most.
Adam and Parvati are angry that
I flopped, and I'm absolutely
convinced I made the right
decision.
Everybody needs a bad guy, so I
become the bad guy, and
everybody else is good, nobody
else has lied, nobody else has
manipulated things.
Everybody knows that's not true.
>> I'm tired.
>> I'm really tired.
>> It was pretty exhausting.
I'm going to try to keep my chin
up and just keep punching.
I don't know how far I'm going
to get, but I know that I'm not
going to let a couple of kids
like that ruin everything I've
been working towards.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Out fishing.
( laughter )
>> Ah!
Oh, my god.
Oh!
What do I do?
>> That is a deep cut.
That is a really deep cut.
>> Pressure.
>> Where is your buff?
We have to have somebody look at
it because that looks too deep.
>> I feel like my finger is
about to fall off.
>> There's a slice through the
nail, pretty close to the middle
of the nail, so we tried to stay
as calm as possible to keep her
calm.
...trying to open up a coconut.
>> Yeah.
>> I think that Parvati needs
medical attention.
>> It's like, literally, you can
see where it's separated, where
the finger is actually
separated.
Oh!
>> Going to have a bit of a look
at it here, and then see what we
need to do.
How did this happen?
>> I was chopping a coconut with
the machete, and I chopped off
my finger instead.
>> You're stitching it right
here?
>> You're being so brave,
Parvati.
>> There is something about
fingernails falling off that
really bothers me, so...
You know, I didn't really want
to look at him sticking needles
under the actual finger that was
dangling.
It wasn't the best sight in the
world, mainly because I was
thinking that, you know, with us
being a dying breed, she doesn't
need to be out there cutting her
fingers off because it's just
her and I against the world
right now.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How is everybody doing?
>> Good.
>> PROBST: What happened,
Parvati?
>> Thumbs up!
I just pulled the old chop-your-
thumb-off-with-a-rusty-machete
trick this morning.
>> PROBST: Can you get it wet?
>> I can get it wet a little
bit.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge,
definitely going to get a little
wet.
For today's reward challenge,
you will use a small bucket to
transport water from the ocean
into a larger bucket.
When you get enough water in the
larger bucket, the weight of the
water will lower the bucket,
raising a flag.
First person to raise their flag
wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The winner of today's
challenge will go to another
island.
Locals will then take you to a
sacred cave, and you'll have a
spectacular picnic.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Fried chicken, meat
loaf, apple pie.
>> Now you're talking.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winner will send one person to
Exile Island.
There's one other element to
this reward.
Jonathan, say hello to your
wife, Stacy.
>> Oh!
( applause )
>> PROBST: It's been 31 days.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Everybody okay?
>> Everyone's great.
>> PROBST: Parvati, say hello to
your dad, Mike.
( applause )
>> Oh, my god!
>> PROBST: Adam, say hello to
your dad, George.
>> He looks just like him!
>> How you doing?
I miss the hell out of you.
You look good.
>> PROBST: Becky, here is your
sister, Sarah.
>> Sarah Lee!
( applause )
( crying )
>> Stop crying.
>> PROBST: Yul, somebody here
wants to say hi to you, your
brother, Paul.
Paul, come on out!
( applause )
>> Oh, god, how are you?
>> PROBST: All right, Ozzy, your
mom's dying to get out here.
Gina, come on out.
( applause )
>> PROBST: Sundra, your mom,
Jeanette.
She's running to see you.
( crying )
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: Okay, the person who
wins this challenge will not
only enjoy the reward.
They will share that reward with
their loved one.
( applause )
>> Oh, yeah.
>> There's one other twist.
Not only will they share the
reward with you, you will
partner up with them for this
challenge.
You are all participating.
Here's how it works: the
survivors will scoop water out
of the ocean.
You will toss it to your loved
ones, who will have to catch the
water and empty it in their
bucket.
The last twist to this
challenge: you will be
blindfolded.
Your loved ones will be your
guide.
>> Oh, of course!
>> PROBST: We'll get you
blindfolded up, and we'll get
going.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Adam, come back.
Throw it straight like shooting
a free throw.
Good job.
>> Up and out.
There you go.
>> You're right.
Good.
>> Was that good?
>> No, that was very diffused.
>> Ready?
>> Yeah, go, go.
All right, a little too strong.
>> PROBST: Everybody trying to
figure out a system.
>> I'm trying to set you up.
>> Going straight.
Come on, throw.
>> I'm missing it.
It's stopping about halfway.
>> To the right!
>> Good, good.
>> PROBST: Who's going to win
this reward?
>> Throw it more straight
forward.
Okay, do it again!
Do it again!
>> That was great.
Do it like that again.
>> Throw!
You're taking too long!
>> PROBST: Ozzy making a little
progress with his mom, Gina.
>> Ready?
>> That's it, arc.
Good.
A little bit higher!
>> Higher, okay.
>> PROBST: Parvati and Mike
starting to do it.
>> Now throw it straight
forward.
>> From down here?
>> Yeah, okay.
>> PROBST: Becky and Sarah
having no luck.
George and Adam not in it right
now.
Ozzy with another good toss to
his mom.
Jonathan and Stacy competitive.
Ozzy and Gina having fun.
>> Need more push, more push,
more push.
>> Am I spraying?
>> Yeah, you're spraying.
That one didn't go anywhere.
>> PROBST: Yul and Paul having
no luck.
Jonathan with Stacy.
Stacy using her shirt, wringing
everything out into that bucket.
>> That's a good idea.
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Stacy
with the lead right now.
Gina doing the same thing, using
her shirt, trying to get every
drop in that bucket.
>> Up and out.
>> PROBST: Sundra, Parvati, you
got to pick it up if you want to
win this.
Sundra not in it right now.
>> Keep going, yeah!
We're filling it up!
>> PROBST: Parvati and Mike with
a lot of water.
They're now in this challenge.
Jonathan and Stacy, Ozzy and
Gina, Parvati and Mike, they're
all three in it.
Jonathan and Stacy very close.
Ozzy and Gina, you're falling
behind.
Stacy doing better using her
hair than the bucket.
We're getting very close to
somebody winning this.
Mike and Parvati are very close!
That flag is raising!
You've got to hit the wood.
Jonathan's flag is now raising.
>> Right here, baby!
>> PROBST: It's Jonathan and
Parvati.
Parvati wins reward!
>> Good job, Parvati.
>> I'm sorry, baby.
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Nice job.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: First order of
business: you have to choose one
of these six to leave right now
and go to Exile Island.
>> Jonathan.
>> PROBST: Jonathan not even
asking permission.
He's taking a good-bye.
>> Love you.
>> PROBST: Now to the more fun
part of the reward.
Two other survivors...
( laughter )
...and their loved ones will
join you on this reward.
And, Mike, you're going to
decide who it is with no help
from you.
>> Oh...!
>> PROBST: No talking from the
survivors.
Who are you taking with you?
>> Oh, man.
Uh...
Oh...
Island lady, Jeanette.
>> Oh, beautiful ladies!
>> PROBST: Jeanette, Sundra,
come over here.
( applause )
One more choice.
>> George, right?
>> PROBST: Adam's dad, George.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Loved ones, it's been
a pleasure having you here.
It's time for you guys to go.
You can head back the way you
came in.
Well, the good news is you're
all going back to camp together.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Sundra, Adam,
Parvati, loved ones, boat will
pick you up in a few hours, take
you to your reward.
All right, take them back to
camp, guys.
>> So you're back at camp.
Do you believe I've been here
for 31 days?
>> Yeah.
>> I was, like, squealing and
jumping up and down when I won
because it was just so
unexpected, but I needed it.
It showed me that I am still in
this game and, you know, that
I still have a fighting chance.
This is home.
I'll give you a tour.
Here's the living room.
>> I'm really glad because I
couldn't describe this in words,
I don't think.
It was great to see George here.
George is my dad, and I call him
George because he's my best
friend.
I'm surprised I lasted this
long.
>> Well, I'm proud of you,
buddy.
>> I told you, don't...
The chances of me lasting past
tomorrow are slim.
>> Okay.
>> I could get into this.
>> Yes, for a day.
I think having my mom come here
and see it, it's going to give
her a whole new perspective that
I probably could never get
across.
I mean, this is something that
my mom probably would never have
had in her whole lifetime.
>> Interesting.
That's what we have to drink?
>> Yes, we boil it.
So I think actually we're going
to get some tonight because we
filled up our water bottles.
>> Want to see the house where
we sleep?
>> Yeah.
>> That's awesome!
( laughter )
>> It's kind of annoying having
the camp be overrun with the
competitors' family.
Parvati and Adam depend on the
food that we provide them, so I
almost feel responsible for
helping them be strong enough to
win that challenge.
>> Here it comes.
You ready?
>> All right, bye-bye.
>> Bye.
>> Have a good time.
>> Bye, guys.
>> See you guys later.
>> Me, too.
>> Yeah!
>> It's really nice.
>> I agree.
>> Laid back.
>> Exactly!
>> It was unbelievable.
We got greeted by at least 100
people, women and children, just
singing to us and, like, we were
celebrated.
It was fabulous.
I loved it.
>> We have no idea what they're
singing, you know.
It's just amazing.
The little kids are around us.
And then they walk us to this
cave, and in this cave, there's
fresh water.
It was, like oh, my god!
Like a little piece of heaven
just dropped right off the side
of the road.
>> They do it twice a year, this
religious ceremony where they,
like, bless the cave water, sing
and pray, and it's just a
ceremonial occasion, and I was
so grateful that that was part
of the reward.
And it was like, I mean, just a
once-in-a-lifetime thing that
happened.
( applause and cheers )
>> Whoo!
>> I haven't had fresh water in
32 days.
It was so cool and refreshing.
And when I came up, our skin
smelled nice because of the oil.
It felt so good.
( cheers )
>> The world is getting much
smaller, and it would only
benefit us if we took the time
to learn about somebody else.
Because guaranteed there's at
least one thing that we have in
common.
>> Oh, my god!
Oh, my god!
Are those biscuits?!
It was unbelievable.
The blanket was just full of
fried chicken, meat loaf,
biscuits-- I mean, I'm a
Southern girl.
I love chicken and biscuits.
I am so glad I won that
challenge.
>> As you should.
>> That is good.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Go for it, Adam.
>> Got to beat Jonathan
tomorrow.
That's our goal for the rest of
the time we're here.
We just have to beat him at
everything.
I feel like I'm about to
explode.
>> Oh, gluttony is so good.
Adam and Parvati without
Jonathan around are a lot more
chilled out, and we got a chance
to just talk, find out a little
bit more about each other and
just be really calm.
>> I think we should do
something.
>> All I know is I can't keep
feeding Adam and Parvati and
have them win.
>> You don't think it's fair, in
a sense, to feed people like
your enemies.
>> No, I understand.
Ozzy catches pretty much most
of our food, and Adam and
Parvati keep on winning these
challenges.
So I think at this point, we've
tentatively decided to keep on
catching food, but maybe hide
some of it from Adam and
Parvati.
>> I think we should just throw
them in the woods.
>> Right there.
>> Now is a key, pivotal moment,
and I don't want to feed people
that beat me.
So for Adam, Parvati, and
Jonathan, no more coconuts.
They can go get their own.
>> How was it?
>> Hi!
>> Hi, Parvati.
>> Hi, guys.
How are you?
>> Tell us all about it.
>> This is a survival game, so
the issue is just trying to have
an upper edge in the game and
not feeding someone so they can
beat you.
And Adam is the biggest guy, and
he eats the most.
And so the less food he eats,
the more drained he gets.
>> If you can't get your own
food at this point, then maybe
you shouldn't be in the game.
>> Oh, my god!
Oh, my...
Thank you!
>> I'm not done yet.
>> Oh, my god!
The original plan for Ozzy and
myself and also Yul was to sort
of hide the coconuts, hide the
food, you know, to save it for
us for later.
But after we saw that Adam and
Parvati brought back so much
food, we sort of felt bad.
I think the hiding plan is sort
of on the outs.
>> Guys, thank you, seriously.
>> People seem more chilled out
if we're just our six without
Jonathan, so it's sort of nice
that he's on Exile right now.
>> Oh, Yul's going to cry!
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Jonathan
returning from Exile Island.
>> Thanks, guys.
Hi, guys.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Adam, take back the necklace.
>> No more bling-bling, huh?
>> PROBST: Once again immunity
back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to race out into the water
and maneuver across a series of
obstacles.
When you reach the end, you'll
retrieve a bundle of sticks and
race back.
You must then go out and do this
a second time.
Once you have both bundles back,
you'll untie the sticks and,
using the rope and the sticks,
build one long pole, which you
will then use to retrieve two
rings.
First person to retrieve both
rings wins immunity, guaranteed
a one-in-six shot at winning
this game and the million-dollar
check that goes along with it.
Losers, you know what happens:
tribal council tonight.
Somebody going home.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for spots
and we'll get started.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
Ozzy leading the pack.
He's first to the platform.
Yul up on the platform.
Jonathan right behind.
Yul in the water.
He's got to go back to the
platform.
Ozzy making quick work of this
course.
Not hesitating.
Ozzy in the water, swimming out
to his buoy.
Yul and Jonathan right behind.
Becky, Pavarti, Sundra on the
course.
Yul across the barrels, hanging
on!
Ozzy heading back with his first
bundle of sticks.
Yul swimming out to his bundle.
Parvati and Sundra making their
way across the balance beams as
Ozzy heads back.
Jonathan swimming out for his
first bundle.
Adam slides across the barrel.
Ozzy having no trouble.
Yul heading back with his first
bundle.
Ozzy back with his first bundle.
Becky and Parvati having a hard
time with the barrels.
Jonathan heads back with his
first bundle.
Adam working on the knots of his
first bundle while Ozzy is
getting ready to lap him.
Yul swimming back with his first
bundle of sticks.
Parvati struggling to hang on to
that barrel.
Parvati off again.
She's got to go back.
Yul's back with his first
bundle.
Everybody is having a hard time
with the barrels.
You're being too cautious.
Attack this course.
Jonathan slides across the
barrels.
Ozzy slides across the barrel
and makes it.
Ozzy swimming for his second
bundle.
Adam coming back with his first
Jonathan's heading back.
Parvati makes it across.
She's swimming out for her first
bundle.
Ozzy's back on the course.
Yul across the barrels, swimming
out for his second bundle.
Ozzy passes Adam now, heading
back with his second bundle.
Jonathan taking his time.
Adam in no rush.
Ozzy already untying his
bundles, getting to work on his
pole.
Yul takes a nose dive.
Parvati off again.
Everybody falling.
Sundra takes a hard fall on the
barrels.
Lots of bumps and bruises.
Adam back with his first bundle.
Ozzy spacing it out, trying to
get an idea of how much pole he
has to work with.
Parvati back with her first
bundle.
Yul back with his second bundle.
He starts working on his pole.
Becky finally back with her
first bundle of sticks.
Down to Ozzy and Yul.
Who will get their pole together
first?
Whose will be strong enough to
work?
Ozzy's got his pole together.
Giving it a go.
Ozzy with his first ring back.
Ozzy doing it all with the pole.
Ozzy very close.
Ozzy wins immunity!
Ozzy, come on over.
( applause )
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Once again, Ozzy is
safe tonight at tribal council.
Out of curiosity, anybody here
overly concerned that by not
winning they're in trouble
tonight?
Adam, Parvati.
Well, we'll see if your concerns
are warranted.
Tonight, tribal council,
somebody going home.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
See you at tribal.
>> Immunity challenge was right
up my alley.
It was actually quite hilarious
seeing people just eating it all
over the place.
>> Big old nut, isn't it?
>> It's humongous.
>> Big green nuts.
( laughter )
>> How's your sister?
There's clearly something up.
People don't really know exactly
what to say to me, you know?
Something is afoot, no question.
Something has shifted.
How far it's shifted and how
much time I have to correct the
shift, I don't know.
If they're going to vote Adam
off tonight, then I've got two
days.
If they're going to vote me off,
I've got a couple of hours and
probably not a hell of a lot of
chance.
>> Yeah.
>> Great.
>> Some people might be like,
oh, you know, Jonathan's a
weasel and he... whatever,
weaseled his way in, but as far
as locking up the final four, if
Jonathan wasn't in it, who would
get it?
>> He was the only one that we
knew we could flip.
>> I understand that.
I don't think you're a bad
person for that at all.
I think that was good strategy,
it was great strategy.
But at this point, it doesn't
matter.
Why not have me or Parvati in
the fifth spot instead of... as
opposed to Jonathan?
>> Right.
It's a little bit weird for me
because I feel like I'm kind of
like the godfather or something
arranging a hit on somebody and
someone's asking, like, to take
out one person or another.
>> He doesn't deserve it.
>> The truth of the matter is I
don't know if I'm entirely
comfortable with it.
I will do everything I can to
keep you here because that
serves my interest.
>> I appreciate it.
>> If I can't...
>> Listen, clearly, the energy
has shifted.
And, you know, obviously, my
time away was a bad time to be
away.
You had a feast, you had guests,
you had food brought back for
you, and Parvati and Adam are
charming young people, they're
closer to your age than I am, et
cetera, et cetera.
But let's... you know, let's not
be stupid, please.
You know, I'm the perfect person
to keep around.
I'm not a threat in terms of
immunity.
And I saved your hide.
And I was happy to do it because
I felt like it made amends for
my stepping away, you know, and
they're going to say anything
they can.
Because if you fall for it, then
I'm gone, and they're still
around in the game, waiting to
take you guys out.
It would be stupid to vote me
out because I came back and I
saved my alliances' lives.
Are they really going to
sacrifice themselves and all
they've worked for because
Parvati is smiling at them now?
You know, because Adam is
stepping up and gathering a
little bit of wood?
>> Yeah.
It's either Jonathan or Adam,
because they seem to be the
biggest competitors right now.
It's really hard to pick,
though, which one is worse.
I think that, you know, as long
as the girls stay... stay
cool...
I think they will.
>> I think we're kind of set
anyways, right?
>> We're set...
>> I think the final four is
pretty much...
As long as no one does anything
crazy and the girls break, we're
there.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury: Brad,
Rebecca, Jenny, Nate, and
Candice, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Pavarti, let's talk about the
reward.
Which was better, spending time
with your loved one or all that
food?
>> Hands down, spending time
with my dad, you know.
Seeing just the joy on their
faces.
They're so proud of us and what
we're doing right now.
You know, and then when we went
on the reward and we were, like,
being celebrated with the
villagers, and biscuits, fried
chicken, apple pie-- you can't
really beat it.
>> PROBST: Adam, at this point
in the game, a good meal can
have a direct impact on the next
challenge.
>> You know, Ozzy didn't go to
the reward and he won the
challenge, so I don't know if
that's a good theory or not.
But I think it's more of going
to Exile Island damages you for
the immunity challenge more than
getting the reward helps you.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
Exile Island.
Parvati, why Jonathan?
>> Sending Jonathan was a
strategy move to keep myself in
the game as long as possible.
I'm hoping that they'll begin to
see, you know, life is better
without him and keep me and
Adam.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, nice not having
Jonathan around camp for a
while?
>> Sure.
>> PROBST: Why?
>> Jonathan's got a very strong
personality, and sometimes it's
hard to be around.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, are you
learning stuff about yourself
that you didn't know, or have
you heard this kind of stuff
before?
>> Well, I mean, I am
disappointed and surprised to
hear that these two have had as
much influence on these guys and
that a day or two in camp, or
three or four, whatever, is
going to throw out the trust
that I put in them and the flop
that I made for them.
But I don't know if that's going
to happen.
I really hope it doesn't.
>> Once again, Jeff, just like
last tribal council, no one
wants Jonathan around.
Just the fact that there's six
good people out here that really
deserve to be here.
>> Why don't I deserve to be
here?
>> Just your integrity.
You don't have any.
You flop all the time, and it's
frustrating, every time we come
to tribal council to see them
over there, and he should have
been voted out each time they
were voted out.
>> You know, I beg to differ,
okay.
All of the people that were
voted off from Raro were not
voted off only by me, you know.
I was in a desperate situation
where I had come over there, and
it was their tribe mates who
voted for them.
>> PROBST: Do you feel a bit of
a debt is owed to you for saving
them and giving them the chance
to win this game when they
didn't have it?
>> Um, yes.
Some of them would not be here
tonight if I hadn't flopped.
That's just the truth.
But the fact is I have earned
my right to sit here tonight,
and I believe I have earned a
right to sit here at the next
tribal council.
>> PROBST: Yul, Jonathan says
that he saved you guys, and yet
I've heard you say that you
saved Jonathan?
Who saved who?
>> I think we both saved each
other.
I mean, our backs were against
the wall, and we had to make
moves out of desperation.
So I would say collectively the
four of us, the Aitutaki four,
are in control of the game to
the extent I have the idol and I
have a lot of influence within
that.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Ozzy, you have the individual
immunity necklace.
I don't assume you're giving it
up to anybody.
You cannot vote for Ozzy.
We also have the hidden immunity
idol.
If whoever has it needs it
tonight, you'd present it to me
after the vote.
You would be safe, and the
person with the next highest
number of votes would be sent
home.
It is time to vote.
Becky, you're up.
>> Uh, what can I say?
You're the biggest threat to me.
You deserve to go home.
>> ( whispering ): You should
have been voted out a long time
ago.
Hopefully we got it right this
time.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jonathan.
Adam.
One vote Adam, one vote
Jonathan.
Two votes Jonathan, one vote
Adam.
Jonathan.
Three votes Jonathan, one vote
Adam.
14th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury:
Jonathan.
That's four, that's enough,
unless you have the hidden
immunity idol.
Please bring me your torch.
Jonathan, the tribe has spoken.
>> And I'd like my hat back at
some point.
Good night, guys.
>> PROBST: Interesting tribal
council.
You vote out somebody who
thought he could trust you,
which now means trust should be
an issue for every single person
left in this game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> We're the underdogs.
We got to fight.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: Parvati and Adam
develop a plan.
>> Is there any way you'd vote
any of them?
>> I'm going to do whatever I
can to win.
I don't care what that means.
>> I'm scared of Ozzy.
>> PROBST: And Becky and Yul
consider turning on Ozzy.
>> It's up to you.
I'll leave it... whichever way
you want to do it.
>> These people are terrible
liars-- terrible liars.
I wish they'd told me to my face
but they didn't do that because
then there would be an argument
and obviously they didn't want
to hear me talk anymore.
So now they'll have a peaceful
camp and they'll have to deal
with each other stabbing each
other in the back as if that's
some new thing in the game of
Survivor.
Four of those six people are
going to join me on the jury
soon enough.