>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
survivor...
>> Let's get some firewood going
here.
>> PROBST: ...at Raro...
>> We have to get it together
today.
>> PROBST: ...Jonathan's
direction turns some people off.
>> Don't be coming around
barking orders at me in the
morning.
It's like "Shut up, fool."
>> PROBST: Drop your buffs.
You are merging.
Raro and Aitu became one.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> PROBST: There is a large
native catamaran filled with
food.
( laughter )
Though the merged tribe
celebrated, the outnumbered Aitu
four felt vulnerable.
>> Our backs are against the
wall.
We need someone to flip.
So I think I know what would
change the game.
>> PROBST: Yul formulated a
plan...
>> I have the idol.
>> PROBST: ...to use the hidden
immunity idol as leverage.
>> I think I can use it to get
Jonathan.
If it works out, it could change
the course of the game.
Hypothetically, say I have the
idol...
>> I'd have to think long and
hard about my reaction if you
even implied that you could show
me the idol.
>> PROBST: At the first
individual immunity challenge...
We are down to the final two.
...Candice and Ozzy battled it
out.
But in the end...
Candice drops out.
Ozzy wins the first individual
immunity.
You are safe in tonight's vote.
After the challenge...
>> This is the idol.
>> PROBST: ...Yul tried to seal
the deal with Jonathan...
>> I appreciate you showing that
to me.
Basically, Yul said, "Vote with
us, or you're going home
tonight."
>> PROBST: ...while Candice and
Adam were playing their own
game.
With tribal council looming...
>> Please understand I have to
think about this.
>> PROBST: ...Jonathan was the
swing vote that would make all
the difference.
>> Either way, people are going
to be pissed.
Either I'll have betrayed the
Raro people and I'm a complete
bastard, or I didn't jump over
to the Aitu people and I'm a
complete bastard.
>> PROBST: But at tribal
council, when it came time for
his decision...
12th person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury...
...Jonathan betrayed his former
Raro tribe and joined the Aitu
four in voting out Nate.
Nate, the tribe has spoken.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> All I can tell you is this.
You ready?
If it wasn't going to be me
tonight, it was going to be you.
>> He was going to play the idol
tonight.
You know?
I was not going to play that
game, because the next time, the
four of them are gunning for me,
and I'm in a tie-breaker
situation.
So I either had a 100% chance of
going home tonight or a 50%
change of going home the next
time.
Because I wanted to swing the
vote, flip the game, I vote for
Nate.
And the truth is that I would
rather play with the Aitu
people; I'd rather see them win,
if I don't win.
I was in the position to make
that choice, and I did, and I
believe I made the right choice.
>> So at tribal council, I think
everyone was holding their
breath.
I believed Jonathan, and I
believed he was sincere in
switching over, but I wasn't
sure.
>> It was a huge risk that we
took.
But this is how I wanted to play
the idol.
I wanted to play it at a point
in time where it, you know,
resets the entire game in your
favor, and it worked.
>> You pissed everyone in this
game off, so I hope you're happy
with second place.
I just think that you played
yourself out tonight, and I am
so disappointed.
It's vile to me.
It makes me... I feel sick to my
stomach.
After tribal, I just felt like
that nausea, and I... really,
all I wanted to do was take
Jonathan's face and just throw
up all over it.
You weren't going home tonight.
>> I could have been going home
tonight.
>> No, you couldn't have.
>> If I didn't throw in with
them, they all would have vote
for me.
You all would have voted for
Yul, and it would have bounced
off Yul and hit me.
>> Not if you told us about the
idol.
>> Yul doesn't have the idol.
>> Yul does have the idol.
He showed me the idol.
I don't know what you think
you're talking about.
And even my saying that, you
wouldn't trust that I was
telling the truth.
>> I don't.
I absolutely don't trust a word
that comes out of your mouth.
>> Fair enough.
>> I couldn't control myself.
I snapped on him and told him
how I felt about him and called
him out.
And I think that he's a filthy,
miserable rat.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> It kind of grosses me out,
but I'm going to watch.
>> You reach inside, and you
just pull out...
>> Ew!
>> I'm guessing this is day 28.
Parvati had never gutted a fish
or even seen how to gut a fish
in 28 days out here.
Now, I don't know how that's
possible.
>> What is that thing?
>> Oh, and you guys eat that.
Candice eats it.
>> She's a lazy, selfish girl,
and a million dollars to her
would not help her in her life.
It would screw her life up.
She's been here 27 days, and she
never gutted a fish, never even
saw how to gut a fish?
>> I was teaching her how to gut
a fish.
>> You didn't see me showing
her?
>> And she's was like, "Ew."
>> This game is not as fun in
this position.
>> I know.
>> Gross.
He makes me want to throw up.
>> It's a social game.
I love playing with you guys.
I love hanging out with you.
We all worked well, together.
Do you know what I mean?
We had it down.
I come over here, and I see that
I'm in the clown house.
>> PROBST: Come on in.
Have a seat.
Nice, hot, muggy day, perfect
for a Survivor auction.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: You each have $500.
Bidding is in increments of $20.
Borrowing money is okay.
Sharing food is not.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Auction will end
without warning.
Ready to get started?
>> Yup!
>> PROBST: First item...
>> $20.
>> PROBST: $20 to Jonathan.
>> Oh, we don't know what it is.
>> PROBST: No, you don't.
>> 60.
>> 80.
>> 100.
>> PROBST: $100 to Jonathan.
Going once, twice, sold to
Jonathan.
Come on up.
Right in here is a slot.
Thank you, sir.
You want to see what you bought?
>> I certainly do.
>> PROBST: Hot dog, fries, and
to go along with it, cold beer.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, snap.
>> PROBST: Take it.
Sit on down.
>> Oh, it smells good.
>> Oh!
>> Party foul.
>> Spill it on me!
>> PROBST: Next item a little
Different.
Next item...
>> Oh, a bath tub.
>> PROBST: The next item is a
hot bubble bath.
>> You sit right here and take a
bath?
>> And while you're taking your
bath, you will enjoy a huge
piece of chocolate cake!
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my god, no!
>> I'm in it.
I'm in this game.
>> PROBST: Start the bidding.
>> 20 bucks.
>> 100 bucks.
>> 160.
>> Adam!
Wait a minute!
>> I stink.
>> 200.
>> 220.
>> 240.
>> 300.
>> PROBST: Jonathan!
Out of nowhere, the guy nobody
wants to see take a bath now
leading the auction at 300.
>> 320.
>> 340.
>> PROBST: The question is does
Jonathan really want it, or does
Jonathan want you to spend all
your money?
>> 360.
>> PROBST: 360 going once, going
twice, sold for $360 to Parvati.
>> Oh, man.
>> 360, take your cake.
The bath is yours.
>> Wow, that's huge!
>> Oh!
>> She's in her element, you
see.
She's happy.
>> I love this day.
It's my favorite day.
>> Let's keep this thing going.
I'm hungry.
>> PROBST: Next item, this will
give you power in this game.
That's the only clue I'm going
to give you.
>> 100.
>> 200.
>> 400.
>> PROBST: 400 to Jonathan.
>> 500.
>> PROBST: Candice bids
everything she has.
>> Becky, I'll lend you money.
>> 600.
>> Becky, out of nowhere,
borrowing money.
She's at 600.
>> Why do you need that, Becky?
Y'all have the numbers.
>> PROBST: Candice now looking
to Adam for a loan.
>> 620.
>> PROBST: 620 to Candice.
>> 640.
>> PROBST: 640.
Going once, going twice...
Adam and Candice shake their
heads.
They don't want anymore.
Sold to Becky, $640.
It's all there?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Open the note and
read it here.
>> "You must send one person to
Exile Island immediately and
take the rest of their money for
yourself."
>> Oh!
>> Yeah, whoo!
>> PROBST: Who's it going to be,
Becky?
Who's going to go to Exile
Island, leaving right now?
The rest of their money goes to
you.
>> They both have $500.
>> Candice.
>> PROBST: For the fourth time,
Candice going to Exile Island.
What are you thinking right now,
Candice?
>> Just some food.
>> PROBST: Now, it is day 29.
There is still the idea of the
hidden immunity idol out on
Exile.
>> I think I know where it is.
>> I can end the suspense.
I have it.
>> PROBST: You have the idol.
>> I have the idol.
>> PROBST: Did you bring it with
you?
>> Uh, yeah, it's in my bag.
>> PROBST: You want to show it
to us now?
>> Sure.
>> PROBST: You want everybody to
know, we might as well just make
sure.
>> Wow.
>> This is it right here.
It's a compass on the necklace.
>> Looks authentic.
>> PROBST: Yul, why did you want
everyone to know something
that's so valuable?
>> I wanted to play it at a
critical moment in a game.
That opportunity came up, when
we were down in the merge.
We came in with lower numbers--
four, five.
We had to make someone switch,
so at that point, I felt like
"This is the right moment.
If I play this right, it could
change the entire ending of this
whole adventure."
And fortunately, it did.
>> PROBST: All right, Candice,
you've given your money to
Becky.
Follow the path.
The boat will pick you up.
You will return in time for the
next immunity challenge.
>> PROBST: Ready for your next
item?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Something else a
little unusual, a never-ending
ice cream maker.
>> Holy...
>> Whoa!
>> Oh, my god!
>> PROBST: For as long as we are
at the challenge, you can eat
ice cream.
>> 400.
>> PROBST: 400, Jonathan,
everyone penny he's got.
>> 420.
>> PROBST: 420, the magic
number, going once, twice, sold
to dolphin boy.
( laughter )
>> Don't waste time!
Don't be funny!
Eat, eat!
Yeah, don't mess around.
>> PROBST: Next item will remain
covered.
>> 160.
>> 180.
>> 200.
>> 240.
>> PROBST: 240 to Jonathan.
Going once, going twice, sold to
Jonathan.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, it's what I like too.
It's got pepperoni on it.
Pepperoni pizza.
Oh, my favorite!
And no sharing, right?
Oh, my god.
>> PROBST: Next item up for bid,
also covered.
>> 60.
>> 80.
>> 100.
>> 120.
>> 140.
>> PROBST: 140 to Sundra.
Going once, twice, sold to
Sundra, $140.
Something straight from your
beach, a sea cucumber.
A little something to clean up
after eating.
>> 100.
>> PROBST: And nobody
interested.
>> PROBST: Do you have $100?
>> I just bid it.
>> PROBST: Sold to Jonathan for
100 bucks.
>> Here's 100.
Here's a tip for you.
>> PROBST: Thanks.
>> Oh, man, if this is the end
of the challenge, I'm going to
jump off a bridge.
>> PROBST: That's it.
Survivor auction is over.
>> Jonathan cleaned up on that
one.
>> I got a hot dog and French
fries.
I got a pizza.
>> The hard part was just
watching other people eat while
you couldn't eat.
>> Of course.
>> That is painful, surprisingly
painful.
I didn't think it would bother
me, but it was actually very,
very difficult.
>> I got to say, I'm much
thirstier having ate that.
I don't know if it's the amount
of food or just the kind of
food.
I wouldn't eat that much food in
the real world.
( burps )
>> Oh, I definitely smell that
pepperoni-- whew.
>> Does this make you guys want
to reconsider the order?
( Sundra sighing )
>> I was just like, "Hmm, maybe
there's a little... a little
resentment, a little hostility
brewing."
>> We just figured, like,
today's show was very...
>> Revealing.
>> ...very revealing.
I think that we were all
surprised.
>> And if he gets in the final
four, I will shoot myself.
Potentially, this game could get
flipped on top of its head once
more-- I'm hoping, I'm praying.
It all hangs on other people
right now.
So the best I can do is try to
be as persuasive as I can and
try not to be pushy.
>> I'm going to get octopus.
>> Okay.
>> It's something that they've
seen.
It's like just seeing the wrong
person get ahead.
I think Jonathan was a little
too arrogant and a little too
cocky at the food auction.
And it just shows a little bit
maybe of what his true character
is like.
>> After today and just... I
feel like his true personality
is coming out.
>> I agree.
>> And actually spending the
last few days with him also is
not something I find
particularly pleasant.
>> Is he coming?
>> So we were just talking
about... talking with Sundra
about the whole order of voting
people out.
>> Cool.
Something is up.
Unfortunately, I think Parvati
and Adam have obviously gotten
in the girls' ear, and I just
don't know to what degree that
has really worked.
Clearly, the energy has shifted.
>> Fourth time coming out to
Exile.
It's tough to keep coming out
here over and over and over
again.
I really miss Adam, and it'd be
really nice, you know, just to
get a hug.
I think I'm next on the chopping
block, and so I need this
immunity.
( thunder )
I wish I wasn't feeling so down
right now.
Emotionally, I'm on the edge.
>> "When were we rolled in a
barrel?
We merged how many days ago?
All these key moments remembered
now become crucial to know.
Your past will affect your
future.
Stay calm, but you better hurry.
Take too long or things don't
add up, you might be the next on
the jury."
>> This challenge is very
important for me personally.
I don't like what Jonathan
stands for.
I don't like having Jonathan
around.
He's just a dirty, dirty rat,
and I would love to get some
revenge against Jonathan and
continue to be in this game.
So I need to win this one.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Now bring in Candice, returning
from Exile Island.
Shall we get to today's
challenge?
>> Sure.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Ozzy, why don't you take that
off?
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
be quizzed on how well you
recollect the events of the last
30 days.
On my go, you will read four
questions.
This will give you answers in
the form of numbers.
You will then add, subtract, or
divide the answers to come up
with a final number.
You'll then untie a
corresponding box, searching for
a key.
You'll use that key to open a
lock, which will raise a flag.
The first three to raise their
flag move on to the final round.
The winner of that round wins
immunity, guaranteed a one-in-
seven shot at a million bucks.
Losers, tribal council, somebody
going home.
Big enough stakes?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, take your
spots on the start, we'll get
going.
Here we go.
First three move on to the final
round.
Survivors ready?
Go.
First question, the total number
of pieces used to construct the
stepping stones for the fifth
immunity challenge used to
transport tribe members from one
platform to the next.
Take that number and add it with
the number of plaster boxes to
be smashed by each tribe with
a club to retrieve keys in the
challenge to win the catalog
reward.
Take those two numbers, subtract
the number of days since the
Aitutaki Tribe mutiny, including
today, and subtract the number
of people currently in the jury,
and you have your number.
How well do you recall what has
happened out here over the last
month?
Jonathan untying, thinks he has
it.
Ozzy untying.
Yul now untying, thinks he has
it.
If you find a piece of metal
that is not a key, you are
wrong.
Jonathan was wrong, has to start
again.
Is Ozzy right?
No.
It's been a long 30 days, hard
to remember everything that's
happened out here.
Parvati, the first one to get it
right.
Parvati moving on to the final.
Two more people moving on to the
final.
Candice close.
Does she have a key?
Who's it going to be?
Adam has a key.
Jonathan has a key.
Candice has a key.
Jonathan is good.
Adam is good.
Candice, just a second too late.
Jonathan, Adam, Parvati moving
on to the next round.
For this round, you will answer
more questions.
You'll use the key to unlock a
timber tunnel, crawl through the
tunnel, over a series of
floating pontoons, and raise one
final flag.
Winner gets immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Here are the next questions: the
number of immunity challenges so
far, including this one, plus
the number of survivors at
tribal council during the lamb
shank feast, divided by the
number of underwater flags
collected in the barrel rolling
competition.
Get that right, you have the
number, you get the key, you win
immunity.
Adam, the first to start
untying.
Parvati, Jonathan, nowhere close
at this point.
Adam is right, he has a big
lead.
And if he's wrong, he'll have to
start over.
Parvati now untying.
Jonathan taking his time,
wanting to be right.
Adam already searching for that
key.
Is he right?
Adam has the key.
He's moving on.
Jonathan untying.
Parvati still trying to stay in
this.
Adam ripping through the knots.
Adam starts through the tunnel.
Jonathan does not have it right.
He's got to do his math again.
Adam up and over.
Parvati has the key.
Adam untying the last knots of
the timber tunnel.
Jonathan, still no key.
Parvati has to untie her knots.
Adam, through the tunnel.
One leg left, the floating
pontoons.
Can he make it in one go?
He's hanging on.
>> You got it.
>> PROBST: Struggling to hang
on.
Trying to crawl.
And he's doing it.
>> Come on!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Adam first to cross,
casually raises his flag.
( applause )
Adam wins immunity!
>> Nice job, Adam.
>> Nice job!
>> Very good job.
>> PROBST: Adam, come on over.
Congratulations.
( applause )
Adam, safe from the vote
tonight.
But here is a fact: one of you
guys is going home tonight.
See you at tribal.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
>> Take a little one, and you
pop it.
>> Welcome back.
>> Thank you.
Adam won immunity today at the
challenge, so tonight we're
going to tribal council, and
it's looking like my number's
up.
It's upsetting to think that
Jonathan will get farther than
me in this game, and that's
upsetting to think that someone
that everyone feels-- everyone,
even the people in his alliance
feel that Jonathan is a snake.
>> Jonathan's just a slime ball,
and he needs to be voted off.
>> I mean, I understand why you
don't like Jonathan, but how
does this help you?
>> I don't care.
>> It doesn't help us...
>> I'll be at peace with myself
if he's voted out before us.
>> Honestly, I will feel like I
have won if he is voted out
before I am.
>> You're an upstanding guy.
>> He's behind you, Yul.
>> Got a flounder.
>> Yeah, my first flounder.
>> Nice.
>> If we can get a fire going,
we can cook some fish.
>> Adam, Parvati, and Candice
approached me today.
They really want Jonathan out of
the game, so they asked me, kind
of appealing to my sense of, you
know, justice and integrity, to
please vote him off first.
Jonathan is not my first choice
to kind of welcome him back.
Like, he's... you know, he is
what he is.
>> I think you're
underestimating him.
>> Let me finish.
I understand how he thinks,
right?
The guy is selfish, and he's
rational, right?
So I can predict, basically,
what he's going to go for.
I can predict, like, what makes
sense to him.
>> I'm not the ring leader.
I mean...
>> Yeah, you are.
>> Let me just... it's not that
simple.
If we change things up right
now, it will have other
ramifications, and you know,
obviously, I can't really talk
about that stuff.
>> Adam was eating that.
Are you taking that away?
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> Yeah, what are you doing?
>> I didn't realize it was your
coconut.
No, no, you eat it.
>> No, I don't want it!
You eat it!
>> Then what's the problem?
All I did was pick it up so I
could share it, that's all.
>> Well, cut it up, eat it.
>> Great, thank you.
>> It's not that complicated.
>> I'll go get some more
firewood so we can make some
fish.
Things finally came to a head.
They've been percolating and
brewing, a lot of silence, a lot
of glares, and I'm getting a
little mad.
( laughter )
>> You did not miss me.
You have not been cuddly.
>> I missed you.
>> And you know what?
You missed your last night to
cuddle.
You missed your last cuddly
chance.
>> I'm uncomfortable!
>> Okay, come here, we'll give
you a smooch too.
>> Jonathan, thank you for the
fish.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you, Jonathan.
>> You're so welcome, guys, of
course.
I wish it could be more.
>> Where'd they all go?
Are they eating?
>> Yeah, probably.
>> That is wrong.
That's coming out at tribal.
All right, I'll be back.
( thunder )
>> What's going on, guys?
>> Well, what do you mean?
>> I mean, since when do you
guys not share food?
This is so arrogant and so rude.
I can't believe this.
>> Didn't you call me a... well,
it doesn't matter.
>> Didn't I call you a what?
>> I was told that I was a
disgusting rat and that I should
be voted against tonight for
whatever reason.
>> Well, Jonathan, you're a rat
because you betrayed everybody
in this game.
>> Okay, well... and yet... and
yet...
>> Everybody knows that you only
care about yourself.
Yul said it this afternoon that
he can predict your behavior
because you're selfish...
>> Self-interested.
>> ...and that you're... so he
knows what you're going to do.
He knows what move you're going
to make because you make the
selfish decision.
>> Candice...
>> And so everybody knows that,
and everybody...
>> Candice, don't speak for me.
I can speak for myself, all
right?
>> Then what did you say?
>> This is not...
>> What did you say?
>> This is not how I would...
>> Look, I said he was a self-
interested, rational player,
right?
To that extent...
>> You said he's selfish.
>> ...I have certainty as to how
he's going to predict... that I
can predict his behavior,
because I know what's going to
like...
>> And you don't like Jonathan,
and you said that too.
And all these people have said
that, that they don't like you.
>> Let's talk about this meal.
We all came home from that...
>> Everybody has their days
where they lay down in the tent.
>> You know what?
That's bollocks, and you know
it.
The rest of us do not choose our
days to go lay down in the tent.
I work my ass off every single
day.
>> Yeah, because you're trying
to weasel your way in somehow.
>> But luckily you're not name
calling, I appreciate that.
>> I'm not.
I'm saying you're trying to
weasel your way in.
>> How dare you...
>> "Weasel" is a verb in this
situation.
>> How dare you imply...
>> Weasel your way in.
>> Excuse me.
How dare you imply that I'm
behaving differently today than
I have for the last 30 days.
You cannot say that that's true.
It's not true.
>> You know...
>> You know what?
And I don't even want to talk
about it.
You've said more than enough for
me.
Thank you.
>> Oh, that's what you're
worried about, thinking they're
going to be mad at you for not
changing your vote?
>> Do it again.
>> But I guess my question to
you is there's three of them.
Are you going to wait until each
one gets voted off to then vote
off Jonathan.
They're basically all saying the
same thing.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury: Brad,
Rebecca, Jenny, and Nate, voted
out at the last tribal council.
I'll remind you, the jury is
here merely to observe.
They're gathering information
for a million-dollar decision.
Let's start with the auction.
Becky, the turning point was
when you sent Candice to Exile
Island for the fourth time.
Why Candice?
>> I think just seeing her
strength and her endurance, she
was probably the fiercest
competitor.
She was the obvious choice.
>> PROBST: Candice, you return
from Exile Island, yet you still
come back with a smile on your
face.
>> I'm out here because I love
this game, and it's been rough,
you know?
There have been some low points.
But like Adam always asks
everybody, "Are you still
smiling?"
And you know, I think you have
to keep that spirit up or else,
you know, you'll collapse.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, what happened
when you got back to camp after
the challenge?
>> I spent a good amount of time
looking for firewood and trying
to get the fire going.
Jonathan went out fishing.
Candice, Parvati, and Adam just
went into the tent basically and
later on caused a huge ordeal
with us five eating fish and
them three not eating the fish.
>> Not sharing the fish.
>> PROBST: You say not eating
the fish.
You say not sharing the fish.
>> Inviting us to dinner,
basically.
>> PROBST: All right, Parvati,
tell me your story.
What happened?
>> Basically, the three of us,
me, Candice, and Adam, know
we're on the outside.
So they have their five, and we
have our three.
And we're in the tent, you know,
just spending time with each
other, you know.
Apparently it pissed some people
off that we weren't helping
around camp.
So Jonathan gets back and
decides that he doesn't want to
share his fish that he's caught.
>> Everybody but Jonathan, I
think, was cool with us working
together.
I think... I mean, haven't
talked to Jonathan, so I don't
know what his thoughts are.
>> PROBST: Are you and Jonathan
not speaking to each other?
>> I don't really care for
Jonathan at this point.
>> It's just interesting the
more comfortable he gets with
his position in this game, the
more his true colors show, and
it just shows the level of
immaturity.
I'm sorry, but I'm half his age,
and I'm twice as mature as he
is.
>> I agree.
>> Now it's all starting to come
out.
I understand that you guys are
hurt or disappointed or
whatever.
But you have five people
working, and you have three
people who don't do any work.
At what point does the five
people who are working and the
three people who are basically
waiting for the dinner bell so
that they can get fed-- you
know, when is that not
appropriate?
>> I think it's an arrogance
thing.
"We got the numbers.
You're going down.
You're on a sinking ship.
You know, we got the food.
We don't have to feed you."
And you know, all of them have
said that they don't like
Jonathan.
>> Everyone knows how you are.
It's not a secret.
>> What am I?
>> You're a rat!
I mean...
>> That's a fact, that I'm a
rat?
I don't even know what that
means.
>> You're just...
>> I'm a cancer.
I know.
That's enough out of you.
>> Is that right?
There's absolutely no reason for
you to be around now though.
>> Says you, jack-- says you.
I've earned my place here today.
>> Jonathan, you have.
You have outwitted your place...
>> Oh, come on.
>> ...to be here today.
>> You're just tired of hearing
the truth, man.
The truth hurts, doesn't it?
>> That I'm a rat and a cancer?
>> Come on.
>> That's the truth?
>> You are.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Well, just sitting
here, it seems to me that rather
than a tribe of five and a tribe
of three, there's a tribe of
three, with Adam, Candice and
Parvati, a foursome with Ozzy,
Sundra, Becky, and Yul, and
there's Jonathan on the other.
>> I would disagree.
>> PROBST: Well, you're the UN.
I'm expecting the UN to come in
here and make everything nice.
( laughter )
>> Look, I mean, obviously when
we tell them things, right,
we're going to do it in a way
that's going to serve our own
interest.
So, you know, I wouldn't take
them at their word.
The way they're painting the
picture is not accurate.
I'll leave it at that.
>> He's the puppet master, and
we're all puppets in his little
play.
>> Come on, what do you expect
me to do?
Look, we're all here trying to
win.
You can't fault me for that.
>> I do not at all.
I respect completely all four of
you.
>> And I'd have a lot more
respect, and so would the people
on the jury, if they cut loose
of their cancer that they have
hooked on them.
>> Even if all three of us were
next to go.
>> Yeah, one, two, three after
that.
>> Boom, boom, boom, sitting
ducks.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, a lot has
been said tonight.
You have been the hub of 90% of
it.
How are you feeling right now?
>> I feel fine.
I mean, you know, one never
wants to hear some of the names
that I've been called, you know.
So what am I going to do?
Move on with the game.
Luckily for me right now, I'm in
a better position than I was
when I was with them.
>> PROBST: Candice, what are you
basing your vote on?
What can you guys do to try and
turn this?
>> Jeff, we've tried everything,
but they're going to vote how
they're going to vote, and maybe
they're going to vote with us,
and maybe they're not.
I just wanted to say that this
is a decision that the jury is
going to make.
They need to know what's really
going on around camp, because
it's been kind of ugly.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
the vote.
Adam, you have the immunity
necklace.
Do you want to give it up?
>> I'm keeping it.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Adam.
There is also the hidden
immunity idol.
You all know that Yul found it,
but he could have given it to
someone else.
Whoever is in possession of the
idol, if you need to play it
tonight, you would present it to
me after the vote.
The person with the next highest
number of votes would be sent
home.
It is time to vote.
Ozzy, you're up.
>> I'm not going to sacrifice
myself for you, and tonight, you
showed me your true colors.
>> Wow, piece of work.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jonathan.
Candice.
One vote Jonathan, one vote
Jonathan.
Two votes Jonathan, one vote
Candice.
Two votes Candice, two votes
Jonathan.
That's three votes Jonathan, two
votes Candice.
Candice.
We're tied, three votes
Jonathan, three votes Candice.
Candice.
That's four votes Candice, three
votes Jonathan.
13th person vote out and the
fifth member of our jury,
Candice.
That's five, that's enough.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, you need to bring
me your torch.
Well, the kiss is nice.
Maybe if it were love, he'd have
given you the immunity necklace.
Candice, the tribe has spoken.
>> Still smiling, guys.
Have fun.
Love ya.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
Well, I think tonight's tribal
council speaks for itself.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> Ah!
I feel like my finger's about to
fall off.
>> That could be bad.
I mean, I don't know if you can
stay out here with that.
>> PROBST: And Yul feels the
pressure.
>> They're going to say anything
they can, because if you fall
for it, then I'm gone; they're
still around, waiting to take
you guys out.
>> I feel like I'm kind of like
the godfather or something,
arranging a hit on somebody.
>> Wow, what can I say?
What a fabulous time I've had
out here playing this game.
I think I can look myself in the
mirror and be comfortable with
the way I played this game,
definitely.
That little kiss with Adam, it
was a nice way to leave.
We were partners through this,
and it was sincere.