(tribal-style singing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> JEFF PROBST: This ship is
cutting through the remote
waters of the South Pacific,
heading to the Cook Islands...
where these strangers have
volunteered to be marooned for
the next 39 days.
>> Stand by, guys.
>> PROBST: This is their story.
You are witnessing 20 Americans
begin an adventure that will
forever change their lives.
>> Hey, you see a little bucket?
>> PROBST: They've been given
two minutes to salvage whatever
they can off this boat.
(chickens squawking)
You need to catch that chicken!
That is food you are gonna want.
There are various items to help
them.
Hawaiian swings, firewood, fish
traps, bananas, lanterns, but
not enough to go around.
They're gonna have to work
together quickly...
>> We've got to find food.
>> PROBST: ...or they'll be left
without.
They have been divided into four
very unique tribes:
Asian American, Caucasian,
Latino and African American.
>> Watch it, watch it, watch it!
>> PROBST: It is a social
experiment like never before.
Each tribe will live on their
own island.
For the next 39 days, they will
be abandoned and left to fend
for themselves.
But this is more than just a
test of survival skills.
This is also a test of social
skills.
>> Watch your head!
>> PROBST: Out here, it's the
impressions you make on the
other castaways that determine
your fate.
Let's go!
30 seconds!
>> Where's the chicken?
>> Forget about the chicken.
Let's go!
>> Someone stole the chicken.
>> PROBST: 20 strangers, forced
to work together to create a
new society while battling the
elements and each other.
Get overboard!
>> Come on, come on!
>> PROBST: Time is up.
They must learn to adapt or
they'll be voted out.
In the end, only one will
remain to claim the
million dollar prize.
39 days, 20 people, one
survivor.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
(murmuring)
>> My first thought when I saw
the tribes were split right
along racial lines was, "Oh,
God, this is gonna be hard."
Just because I-I-I feel like
as a people that have the same
ethnicity, maybe we'll kind of
clash on things.
(grunting)
>> I could care less about
divisions by ethnicity.
When it comes to surviving, it's
a human effort.
(chuckles)
>> Row, row!
>> The Asian invasion.
>> Row!
>> I honestly was stunned.
I mean, this is crazy.
I mean, I... you know, on one
hand, I think it's a great
opportunity, because I think
it's wonderful that there's more
minorities.
Uh, at the same time, I'm a
little bit worried that it might
play out to caricatures and
stereotypes, so I don't know,
it'll be interesting to see
how things play out.
(screams)
>> Different ethnic groups.
I mean, is that... kosher?
(laughing): I don't know.
But it's a cool social
experiment, I think.
>> ...and paddled their way away
from an island, just so I could
have a good life, and here I am
paddling back to an island.
>> Well, where are you from?
Where are your parents from?
>> Uh, Dominican Republic.
When the tribes were divided, I
thought, what an advantage for
the Hispanics.
The Hispanics all come from
Caribbean or South American
backgrounds.
So we're-we're used to being in
this tropical setting.
>> Why don't you guys...
>> One, two, three.
>> This is a unique opportunity
to represent our community in a
positive way.
I mean, we just show that we
work hard and we play hard.
I think we're going to go
pretty far.
>> Building stuff, it should be
the-the shelter, plus I know how
to make a toilet.
>> You want the machete?
>> Well, no, first I'll just
explain it to you, and then
we'll all know what... well,
we'll be on, like, on the same
page.
We'll all have the blueprint.
>> Do you want them with us?
>> Billy said that he can chop
things down and make a hut and
make a toilet, and I was
really fired up.
You know, I mean, I didn't want
to judge him on his appearance.
I mean, he's out of shape.
>> It was kind of obvious to
me, just from the way Billy cut
the bamboo, that he didn't
really know exactly what he was
doing.
>> See, look-- boom, perfect.
>> All right.
>> I had to kind of take over
and build the shelter.
I'm kind of trying to guide
things without trying to step
into a position of being a
leader because I don't want
to... I do not want that to
happen.
>> You guys want some coconuts?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, you want to climb it?
>> Try that.
>> Oh, my God!
>> When I was going up the tree,
it was, uh, a straight picture
right out of The Jungle Book.
All I thought was Mogli going
up the tree.
Watch out.
>> Okay, go ahead.
>> Good.
>> Awesome.
>> I mean, he may not be very
big, but he's an athlete, and
he's somebody who'd be pretty
good at this game.
>> Really good job, man.
>> Good job, dude.
>> I think we're all going to
be able to work as a team, and
I think that we have the
strongest tribe out of anybody
else.
As long as we stay fed and happy
with each other, then we're
going to be able to stay really
strong.
>> Ay!
>> Salud!
>> Ay! Ay!
>> Ay!
>> We did most of the work.
>> I'm not a first-generation
American.
I'm not even an immigrant.
I'm a refugee.
I came, uh, after the Vietnam
War as a refugee.
I'm a survivor in that way.
I've survived the Vietnam War.
I can survive this.
The Puka Tribe is actually an
advantage.
We fly under the radar.
Nobody suspects these little
people with slanted eyes to see
anything or to be strong enough
to do anything or maybe don't
even speak English.
People always underestimate the
Asians.
>> What's your name?
>> Yul.
>> Yul, I'm Cao Boi.
>> Brad.
>> Brad?
>> Yeah.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Becky.
>> Becky, Cao Boi.
>> Jenny.
Okay, we've got time to get to
know each other.
Jenny?
>> Our tribe, Puka, is comprised
of five Asians.
I'm Filipino, Yul is Korean,
Becky is Korean.
Um, Brad is a mix Filipino,
Hawaiian, and Cao Boi is
Vietnamese.
We're a mixed group ourselves,
you know, within the Asian
community.
>> My grandmother's knife is
sharper than this.
You know, I was...
In Vietnam, there's this monk.
He lived for many years on
coconut only.
>> I have a feeling you are
gonna be telling a lot of
stories tonight.
>> Um, I gotta say, just for me,
I'm just.. the person I'm having
the most difficulty with is Cao
Boi because I sense a-a little
bit of a schism there.
I think there's some degree of a
generational gap.
>> My biggest concern being an
all-Asian tribe is I've never
been accepted by the Asian
community.
Take one look at me.
I don't look educated.
I don't fit the stereotype:
hard working, Mr. Engineer with
jacket, suit and tie, drive nice
cars.
I just don't fit the stereotype.
I belong in a hippie
community instead.
It's a very dangerous position
for me to be in.
>> The accommodations are
lovely.
>> Here we are.
>> Yeah-hoo!
>> I guess this is where we're
going to make our shelter.
>> Come on, let's put our hands
together.
>> We made it, and we will
continue to make it.
>> Day one, to the end.
>> To the final end.
>> Absolutely.
>> 'Cause y'all know what this
is about, right?
>> Yeah, we do, sir!
>> Represent, represent,
represent, represent.
>> Whoo, got a new chant!
>> That's what I'm talking
about!
>> I believe we all feel the
pressure to represent, and that
just means it's-it's just being
able to represent us, our
people, the African American
culture.
>> Let's get firewood.
One person get firewood, one
person get bamboo, and the
other person gets, uh, palms.
>> Okay.
>> Here, I don't need this.
I'll-I'll get the palms.
It makes me feel like, because
we are divided by race, now we
have to step up to the plate
and show that, yes, black people
do swim.
Yes, black people do know how
to get on a boat and paddle.
I mean... (laughs)
we don't just run track.
>> We almost got us a house.
>> Yes, honey.
>> Exactly.
>> That's some nasty hair right
there.
>> With our group, it has
nothing to do with race.
We are just a bunch of city
kids.
This couldn't cut cotton.
We're gonna have to sharpen it.
It's not that we are black.
We're just city slickers thrown
into the bareness of life.
Lay... I would lay one here, lay
one here, lay one here, and just
put palms over it and call it a
night.
That's what I would do, but,
it's up to y'all.
>> We just got here.
We're trying to assemble
shelter.
It's going all right.
But, you know, black people
don't like to be told what to
do, and we have a bunch of
headstrong people around here,
me being one of them, I will
say.
>> Uh-uh.
>> 'Cause what happens is we
have...
>> I will not...
No, this is not going to work.
>> We got that part, so we want
to...
What, you want to go like this?
>> Yeah.
>> I think...
>> My vision, well...
I had a dream!
(laughter)
>> Wake up!
>> "Sekou" means leader
and warrior-- I do bring some
leadership, and I've been able
to pull this group's attention
into the focus of what needs
to be done, and they've been
able to respond.
Let's get some palms up, girls.
I wanted us to stay focused for
what we had to do, and I think
I accomplished that.
I'm liking this already.
It may have set a tone, too, and
if it did, I hope it, you know,
was positive for them as much as
it was for me.
>> Pretty impressive.
>> This is low-income housing.
(laughter)
>> How you doing back there?
>> I'm doing great.
>> Okay.
>> The tribes were obviously
divided by ethnicity, but it
doesn't matter to me if it's
just all other white people
or-or, uh, any other type of...
of race.
The issue is what kind of people
you have in your tribe, and what
kind of personalities, and how
you get along with them.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> Here we are.
>> Do we anchor this thing?
It is going to be a true social
experiment.
It's going to be fascinating to
see how it plays out, but I
don't believe that just because
these groups have the cultural
similarities that that will
make them more specifically
cohesive.
This is Survivor.
Somebody is going to win a
million dollars, and they're
going to have to cut the throat
of the guy next to them at some
point.
>> Great haul!
>> Whoo.
>> All right.
>> As soon as we got to the
island, we were just pulling it
all in, excited about all the
treasure that we got.
We seemed to have scored with,
uh, two machetes and two, um,
slings and two chickens.
(clucking)
>> Oh.
(giggling)
>> Hey, make sure those chickens
aren't going to get out.
>> Yeah, but...
>> I did grab a chicken.
The chicken was belonging to
the green team.
I didn't even know.
I saw a chicken.
I grabbed the chicken, 'cause
the chicken was free.
>> Y'all kicked ass today.
>> Yeah, can we just say that
for one second?
>> I think we should have a
coconut and toast to our
victory.
>> Let's do that.
To us all.
>> Hey!
>> Cheers!
>> How cool is this?
>> To the whiteys!
>> The whiteys!
>> I was going to say Rarotonga,
but, I mean...
>> We are the Caucasian group.
We've got, like, a jock, and
then we've got the sorority
type, you've got the steady
type, you know, you got the
family man, and then you got me,
who's kind of like the
alternative option.
>> Tell me your name.
>> Jessica, but my friends call
me Flicka.
>> Flicka.
My friend Flicka.
That's easy.
>> My friend Flicka.
I've never seen that flick.
(screaming)
>> (gasps): No! Oh.
(clucking)
(screaming)
>> No! Flicka!
Why did you have to do it?!
>> I am so sorry.
>> I got a chicken in here.
Guys, come around here.
>> Where, where, where?
>> Okay, okay.
Surround this chicken.
>> All right...
>> There's a chicken right here.
Okay, wait, wait, don't scare,
don't scare, don't scare.
>> Did you get him?
>> No, he moved too fast.
>> Oh.
>> I went to pick up the...
and-and they ran out.
I can't even believe it.
>> Oh!
>> One-second mistake cost us
the chickens.
The woods ate the chickens.
They're in there.
And now I hear them.
I scream at them.
(crowing)
So I'm not happy right now with
Flicka.
I can forgive her, right?
But I-I don't have to forgive
her, 'cause she screwed up my
chickens.
>> Ah!
>> You found it?
(whooping)
>> Yeah?
(both laughing and whooping)
>> That's something very nice.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
>> Oh, good going, mama.
Oh, my God.
>> Parasitic paradise.
>> Our water barrel is full of
parasites and extremely dirty,
but a lot of water is in there,
so when we have some fire to
boil the water that we have,
no one has to worry about
getting dehydrated.
>> ♪ We got our water! ♪
(humming)
>> Rebecca is cool.
Rebecca is really cool.
We're both from New York, so
that already has a little
immediate sense of familiarity.
She's just smart, athletic.
You know, I feel like we can
work really well together.
>> All right, you got it,
Rebecca.
>> There we go, babe.
>> I feel that Rebecca and
Sundra are much closer than I
could be to either of them.
>> I got water! I got water.
>> I'm so proud of you.
>> They go off together a lot.
They're always talking, just
the two of them, so that's just
something that I'm watching.
I'm keeping my eyes on it,
keeping the pulse on it.
>> Did y'all bring back some
water?
>> No, 'cause we don't have
any...
>> We have no fire to boil.
>> Okay...
>> We will work on fire.
We're not going to give up.
>> Okay.
>> Okay? And I'm going to focus
my energy right into the wood.
>> Oxygen...
>> Yeah.
(sighs)
>> Okay, everybody focus, okay?
>> Who's holding the stick?
>> We're making fire.
>> I got the stick.
>> Focus on what we're doing.
>> Are we smoking?
>> No.
>> Come on!
>> Oh, yes!
>> Ooh.
>> I need a break.
>> All right.
>> You want to do it?
>> Yes.
>> It's all you.
>> Building houses, making
fire, in the name of the Lord...
>> Stay cool.
>> He likes to take long breaks,
and we're... It's...
We've got too much to do.
I understand we're all low on
fuel right now, but he is not
one to stay focused at all.
You want something, right?
Sometimes you just have to do it
yourself.
(sighs)
>> It's just very frustrating,
but I'm not going to say
anything more to him right now,
'cause I'm in a state of
pisstation.
(laughs)
>> Can I get a lunch break?
(laughter)
>> It's getting cold out here.
>> Pity the kid...
>> Is anybody else getting cold?
>> I'm freaky cold.
>> Y'all want to go back?
>> Yeah.
>> Should we go snuggle at home?
>> Should we try it?
>> Can we just sleep closer?
I'm so cold.
I get really cold at night, and
so I've been sleeping next to
Adam.
I mean, he's the biggest guy out
here, and he's a good wind
blocker.
Okay, all right, all right,
we're all spooning the same way.
This is going to work.
(laughter)
>> We need to all slide in.
It's cold.
>> Yeah. Slide this way.
>> Adam's an attractive guy.
I mean, he's got a good-looking
face.
You know, he's fit.
I mean, of course, Adam's a
good-looking guy.
>> I'm on fire.
>> I'm... I'm dry.
>> I know you're dry right now.
>> It does make the island a
little more bearable to have a
couple of good-looking girls.
Great-looking girls.
I'm attracted to Candice a lot.
>> It doesn't matter.
It's still warm.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
The body heat is the best thing
by far.
>> Adam wants to be the big,
strong man, and take care of
Candice.
She's, like, a sweet little
girl, and they're snuggling, you
know?
I don't know.
Romance is in the air.
>> Where's the headache?
>> Like, right here.
It's from being seasick all day.
>> Okay, sit down.
Sit down. Sit on...
Brad's problem was he didn't
have the normal headache.
In Vietnamese, we call it a "bad
wind" that's causing him this,
and that results in a headache.
Okay, what I'm going to do is
I'm going to pull this wind out
of you-- this bad wind.
It's not a regular migraine,
on one side or in the back.
It's usually a sinus headache
near the front, and that's an
indicator of the bad wind.
You got it.
You got a touch of bad wind.
It's not real bad, but it is not
great.
There.
You'll feel better now.
Your headache be gone in a few
minutes.
That will go away.
It will fade away.
That's called the indicator.
I just pulled it out of you.
That's how bad you have it in
you.
>> It's not that bad.
>> No.
The I put an indicator here.
By pulling it out, I can see how
bad he has it.
I told him, when it's completely
gone, your body will be fully
healed.
>> What the hell happened to
you?
>> He put his hands all over...
>> What?
And he did that to your face?
>> Yeah.
>> It looks like it's burned!
>> The others-- the Asian
Americans-- they were born in
America.
They've lost touch.
They were not born in the old
country, where a lot of this
stuff is people don't have
antibiotics, so they have to
figure out other ways to do to
get by.
>> You all right?
>> Yeah.
I had a headache, and he got
rid of it, actually.
>> He hit you on the forehead?
>> He was, like, squeezing my
forehead.
I will be truthfully honest
with you.
I did have a headache.
I don't have a headache anymore.
But I do have a red dot on my
forehead.
>> You don't have a headache.
>> I don't have a headache
anymore.
>> You have this red line...
>> That's all right.
>> Cao Boi is an interesting
guy.
When I first met him, I just
kind of wrote him off as a
crazy kook, but in between the
random kind of inane nonsense,
there's actually, like, gems and
nuggets of information that are
actually useful.
>> So, when is it going to go
away?
>> When you're completely
healed.
>> Tree mail.
>> Sweet.
>> Dude, look at all this stuff,
man.
>> Look it, we even got our own
little flag and everything.
>> Yeah.
>> "Life is tough on the island,
and if it's fire that you lack
you can paddle for your food."
Yeah.
>> We're going to a challenge
today that's both immunity and,
uh, reward.
I would like to see us win, but
if we lose, it's not the end of
the world at the beginning of
the game.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Tell me about the marooning.
I want to find out about the
chickens.
Yul, I saw you dive in for one
chicken.
Did you make it back to camp
with it?
>> No.
(laughter)
I got the chicken out of the
water.
I handed it off to a tribesmate,
and next thing I see is someone
else from another team running
around with my chicken.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: What?
Who took the chicken?
>> Where is that fellow?
I think you know.
>> PROBST: Jonathan?
>> Did I?
(laughter)
I had a chicken, but I don't
know, you know.
I mean, honestly, it was so
hectic, that I just grabbed the
chicken.
(laughter)
Sorry, dude.
>> PROBST: Okay, you ready to
get to your first challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Here's how it works.
On my "go," you're going to race
to assemble a puzzle boat.
Once the boat is assembled, use
seven braces to hold the boat
together.
You'll then paddle out and
retrieve fire in the form of a
torch.
When you get back to shore, you
will take those seven braces,
race back to the starting mat,
where you will find four more
puzzles in the form of north,
south, east, and west.
Once you've completed those,
take the braces, use them as
rungs to build a ladder.
Place the compass points in
their appropriate spot, get to
the top.
First three tribes to get all
their tribe members to the top
and light their fire barrel
wins.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First three tribes,
fire in the form of flint.
(applause)
As a bonus, the tribe who
finishes first gets
a fire-making kit.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: A lot of kindling,
water-proof matches, kerosene.
If you can't get a fire going
with that, you need to go home.
(laughs)
Most importantly, you're
playing for what in this game?
>> Immunity.
>> PROBST: Immunity.
The immunity idol is in three
pieces, because the first three
tribes to finish win immunity.
Losing tribe, you get nothing
but a date with me and the
first person will be voted out.
There is one other twist to
this challenge.
The details are here in this
note.
We'll save it until after the
challenge, and then I'll reveal
it.
Okay, for reward and immunity,
survivors ready?
Go!
These boats are puzzles.
They only go together one way.
Puka off to a good start.
>> Bring it over here, you guys.
Bring it over here and do it
over here.
>> PROBST: Aitu getting their
boat together.
>> No, there's another piece.
Another piece.
>> PROBST: Hiki's having a
terrible time.
Raro getting closer.
>> Right there.
>> PROBST: Aitu putting on
their braces, very close.
Puka getting very close.
Aitu has their boat together.
Hiki still having trouble.
Aitu is first in the water,
heading out to their torch.
Puka has their boat together.
Aitu with a big lead.
Rarotonga's heading out to their
torch.
>> Okay.
>> Throw that up here.
>> Which one?
Which one?
>> PROBST: Hiki, work together.
Aitu first to their torch.
Christina in the front.
Puka right behind.
Aitu heading back.
Puka now has their fire.
They're coming back.
Raro cannot get it together
with their paddling.
>> The boat's coming apart.
>> PROBST: Hiki not even
heading out yet.
Let's go!
>> Four. I need four.
>> Four. Four!
>> PROBST: Aitu first back.
Puka gaining some ground.
Raro has their torch.
They're coming back.
Puka's back to shore.
Hiki has it together finally.
Heading out to their torch.
Aitu has their seven braces.
They're heading up.
Raro struggling with their
paddling.
Still in the water, losing a
lot of time.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Billy really slowing
Aitu down.
Puka catching up.
>> Okay, go, go!
>> You going?
>> PROBST: Aitu working on their
puzzle.
Puka working on their puzzle.
You're looking for four
symbols: N-S-E-W.
Hiki has their torch.
They're coming back.
They're still in this challenge.
Raro coming back.
They're heading to the puzzle.
We're neck and neck, Puka and
Aitu.
>> Go north.
>> We got it, baby.
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Adam
working the puzzle for Raro.
Hiki's getting back in this
challenge.
Puka, you're good!
Puka solved all four puzzles.
They're heading up.
Hiki, you're in this thing.
Let's go!
Aitu has it!
They've got all four puzzles!
Aitu gaining on Puka.
>> Let's get first now!
Come on!
>> PROBST: Puka getting closer.
Aitu getting closer.
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Puka moving up.
Jenny's up! Yul's up!
Puka wins the challenge!
Immunity and fire.
We're looking for two more
spots.
Do not quit!
Aitu coming up.
They've got it together.
Aitu wins flint and immunity.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: One spot left.
>> I got it.
>> PROBST: Hiki, you are back
in this challenge.
Raro having a terrible time
with their puzzle.
Lost a lot of time.
>> Don't panic.
>> Don't panic, baby!
>> PROBST: You're good!
Raro has it!
They've got all four puzzles.
They've got to put their braces
in and get to the top.
>> There! No!
>> PROBST: Raro up.
They forgot their puzzle pieces!
Hiki, let's go!
>> Hand them up!
>> PROBST: Candice with the last
piece.
Adam places it in.
Got to get it in!
Raro up.
Harmony's up.
Raro wins!
Puka, Aitu, Raro win immunity.
Hiki, Tribal Council.
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: Okay.
Flint-- Raro, Puka, Aitu.
In addition, Puka, because you
won the challenge, fire-making
kit.
The more important part of
this, immunity.
Raro, safe from Tribal Council.
Aitu, you guys are safe from
Tribal Council.
Puka, because you won, you get
the head of the idol.
Hiki tribe, no fire for you.
No immunity.
A date with me at Tribal
Council.
Somebody going home.
There is one last twist to this
challenge.
I showed you the note
beforehand.
I'll now read it.
"The losing tribe will choose
one person from any of the
"other three tribes to go to
Exile Island."
>> That's what I'm talking
about.
>> PROBST: Here's what that
means.
You're going to choose one
person from one of these other
three tribes.
That person will leave here
right now and spend two nights
on Exile Island.
It is a big disadvantage to be
separated from your tribe this
early in the game.
Exile Island is no picnic.
There is one bag of water out
there.
You will also have a machete, a
flint and a pot.
The silver lining to Exile
Island is, hidden somewhere on
the island is an immunity idol.
That will protect you at Tribal
Council.
It's good up through the final
four.
When somebody finds it, you can
keep that information to
yourself.
You can share it with whoever
you want.
You can even assign that
immunity and give it to
somebody else.
Each time somebody is sent to
Exile Island, you will get a
clue as to the whereabouts of
the idol.
Hiki, who is it going to be?
>> Let's talk this over.
We gotta look at these guys.
We got to take...
We want to...
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: All right.
Back on your mat.
Before you tell me who it is,
it was interesting to note that
the two guys came out here and
made the decision, and the
women stayed back.
>> They seemed like they had
taken control over it.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Who's going to Exile Island?
>> We don't know his name, but
we can point him out to you.
>> We say karma is a bizzle, so
my chicken man over here.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, you're
going to Exile Island.
Grab your stuff.
>> See you guys in two days.
>> PROBST: Take this with you.
Here's your first clue as to
the whereabouts of the idol.
Okay, Hiki, sadly, one of the
five of you will be the first
person voted out of this game.
I'll see you guys at Tribal
Council.
Everybody can head back to
their camps.
>> I think it was because I took
the Asian guy's chicken that
the African-American guys chose
me.
That's all they said.
I was so shocked by what
happened, I didn't even have a
comeback.
"To make a top grade, stand in
a line.
"If the southern isle vanishes,
a salvation you'll find."
The clue that they gave me to
find the idol, I took that to
mean to make the top grade was
an A or an A-plus.
So I started digging.
The idol!
Made sense to me, but I just
haven't found it yet.
I'm cold, miserable, shivering,
missing my wife and kids.
(moans)
Exile Island's really terrible.
>> You guys work on the fire.
We'll continue working on the
bedding.
>> Yeah.
Tonight is the first Tribal
Council, and our tribe, the
Manihiki tribe has to vote
someone out of the tribe.
>> There's no one to blame.
There's...
I guess we just...
>> Yeah. The game begins.
>> Yep.
>> If they're in threes,
they're going to be vote, trying
to vote one of, one of us off.
>> They're stupid if they do
that.
>> They're stupid!
>> So we gotta pull one of the
women.
I don't know, you know, you
never know, though.
These sisters could think,
"Yeah, we don't need no men, we
can do it all ourselves."
>> It's gonna be an interesting
dynamic now.
>> I already feel the tension.
>> Yes.
>> The ladies and I are
thinking that Sekou might be
the right person to vote out at
this time because we've had a
hard time kind of establishing
leadership, and no one's been
working in unison, and we think
that he plays a major role in
that, and it might be easier for
us to work as a team without
him.
>> They may think that they can
get away with losing me or you,
or me.
It ain't going to work.
>> I know.
>> They can't even make fire.
They can't even build a hut,
dude.
I'm telling you.
>> Sundra...
>> And Becca.
and Becca are tight.
>> Right. Right.
>> They're not gonna turn on one
another.
I got that sense.
>> I got that.
>> So...
>> Right.
We know that it's gonna
eventually come down to a
woman-men thing. So...
My plan and Nate's plan was to
make an ally of Stephannie.
If you all lose me tonight, and
y'all lose another competition,
and ultimately y'all will lose
Nathan, and there's just three
girls...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...you're out.
>> Why do you say that?
>> Because them two are tight.
Because them two are like peas
in a pod.
You have to break that up.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Sekou actually came to me
trying to persuade me to align
myself with him and Nate and to
vote Sundra out.
>> We gotta have you, okay?
Now, do you want to make it in a
world with a bunch of people
who got an alliance based on
where they're from, or somebody
that knows how to survive in
this environment?
Or that can bring on some fire?
>> We don't have any fire yet,
though.
>> That's all right.
When I build a fire... (sighs)
y'all better keep it going,
because if y'all boot me out,
there ain't gonna be no more
fire.
This ain't a glamour walk.
This is about survival.
This is the real thing about
getting down.
Do you feel what I'm saying?
>> I do.
>> Okay?
>> I know that my vote is, is a
swing vote.
You know, you've got Nate and
Sekou, you have the men on one
side, you've got Sundra and
you've got Rebecca, the women,
on the other side.
They're very close.
The guys are very close.
So of course I'm the swing vote.
>> Okay?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> All right.
>> We need everybody.
So it's gonna be sad to say
good-bye to somebody tonight.
It's gonna be a little
difficult.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach the flame and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council, because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire,
you're in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
Take a seat.
Well, welcome to your first
Tribal Council.
It goes without saying, not the
place you wanted to be.
So, catch me up.
Rebecca, did anybody step up
right away as a leader?
>> Yes. Sekou definitely
stepped up as a leader and
tried to help structurally
sound, uh, um, shelter for us.
He seemed at the time to know
the best and the quickest way to
possibly get it together.
>> PROBST: Sekou, did you have a
plan to step up as a leader, or
did you look at the tribe and
say, "I think I'm probably the
best guy for the job"?
>> I just took whatever I knew
and started putting that into
effect, and I think everybody
just gravitated towards that.
I didn't say, "Okay, I'm running
things."
I think it kind of ended up
that way, but we work together
well.
>> PROBST: So, Nate, you're
starting to get to know
everybody.
What's the feeling of this
tribe?
>> We have beautiful spirit.
We are like a little family.
Regardless of what happens
tonight, this crew right here, I
mean, they're, they're real
beautiful people.
>> PROBST: How does tribes
divided ethnically change the
game?
Or does it?
(laughter)
>> Yeah, it does.
>> PROBST: Why is it so funny?
>> Because it is!
(laughter)
I don't know.
It's just something you wouldn't
expect, you know. It's like--
"Okay, we're gonna have to
represent for our people
because, you know, we're put
under the light like that, so
let's see what we can do, you
know?
>> PROBST: So, Sundra, with only
five people, the divisions and
how people pair up becomes very
important.
What did you notice?
>> I noticed right off the bat,
well, Rebecca and I have kind of
bonded.
And then I realized that the
two guys had bonded.
And of course, you know,
Stephannie was apart.
It wasn't like she was excluded,
but I think we kind of sensed
each other's vibe already.
>> PROBST: So, Stephannie, there
are two pairs that are bonded,
and you're not a part of either
one of those groups?
>> Naturally, women are going
to stick together. Um...
And the men will naturally bond
together.
That's just natural.
But I'm the odd man out.
That's kind of strange, and I
kind of wondered about that,
but we're all still together.
>> PROBST: Rebecca, only three
days.
Somebody's going home tonight.
So what do you do in terms of
your vote?
What are you looking at in this
tribe?
>> You look at where we're weak
and what we did wrong over the
last three days, and hope that
in voting, that will somehow be
corrected.
>> PROBST: Well, unfortunately
one of the five of you will
have the distinction of being
the first person voted out.
It is time to vote.
Sekou, you're up.
>> You are our weakest, weakest
link.
>> You are a sweet, sweet man.
We just thought this was the
right move for right now.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote--
Sundra.
Sekou.
One vote Sundra, one vote Sekou.
Sundra.
That's two votes Sundra, one
vote Sekou.
Sekou.
We're tied, two votes Sekou,
two votes Sundra, one vote left.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Cook Islands...
Sekou.
You need to bring me your torch.
Sekou, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
If what you said tonight is
true and you just voted out
your weakest link, then you
should go back to camp a
stronger, more organized tribe.
Good news is, because you've
been to Tribal Council, you now
have fire.
Grab your torches.
(laughter)
Head on back to camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes from
our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on Survivor
>> What do you call a
Vietnamese with three dogs?
>> PROBST: Cao Boi's jokes get
no laughs.
>> A joke is a joke, really.
>> No, it's not.
>> No.
>> No, it's not a joke.
>> I don't worry about what
other people think.
>> PROBST: And Billy's slacking
drives Aitu to drastic measures.
>> Billy's just dead weight.
>> Ozzy really wants to throw
the challenge, but I'm thinking,
you know this doesn't seem
right.
>> I believe a good leader is
one who can instill some
guidance and I'm sure that I
had a real strong effect with
my tribe.
I have no doubt about that.
They saw that I was a real
strong leader.
Well, guess what?
They're going to be a really
strong tribe, and I'm proud of
that.
And my torch may be out, but my
flame is still burning.