>> JEFF PROBST: previously on
Survivor...
>> You snapped at me twice.
>> I said you were annoying.
>> Adam and Christina had it
out.
>> You said I annoyed you.
>> It's your personality.
>> Well, you could have said
something to me.
I never thought that's what they
thought of me.
>> PROBST: At the challenge...
Good news, bad news.
The good news is the winners
will feast.
The bad news is you'll be
feasting at tribal council.
>> Ooh!
>> PROBST: Go!
Aitu endured the physical
test...
Jonathan and Yul taking on Nate.
...and gave Raro a beating.
Aitu wins the challenge!
Here's how it's going to work
tonight.
Aitu will go to tribal council
first.
You will vote somebody out.
You will then enjoy your feast
while listening in on Raro's
tribal council.
On Raro...
>> Would you give me a chance
tonight?
>> PROBST: Christina scrambled
to save herself.
>> I had no idea.
I'm very sorry.
I'm trying to talk to some
people.
And hopefully I won't get booted
out tonight.
>> PROBST: Back at Aitu...
>> I'm going to find a way to
defeat him.
>> PROBST: Thinking Jonathan had
the hidden immunity idol, Cao
Boi dreamed up Plan Voodoo.
>> We force the idol out.
>> I think the plan is
ingenious.
I know neither Jonathan nor
Candice have the hidden
immunity idol, because I have
it.
>> PROBST: But at tribal
council...
The sixth person voted out
of Survivor: Cook Islands...
Cao Boi's Plan Voodoo folded,
and his wildcard personality
finally caught up with him...
Cao Boi, the tribe has spoken.
...and he was voted out.
Well, the hard part's over.
Now for the fun.
Aitu enjoyed a succulent
spread...
>> People in our group plain out
said, "You're annoying."
>> PROBST: ...while listening in
on Raro's brutal honesty about
Christina.
>> Unfortunately, she just found
out our true feelings.
>> PROBST: But before the vote,
another surprise was revealed.
Aitu, you will now kidnap one
member from the Raro tribe.
They will be a part of your
tribe through the next reward
challenge.
Aitu, who are you going to
kidnap?
>> Nate.
>> PROBST: Aitu kidnapped
Nate...
Seventh person voted out of the
Cook Islands...
...and Christina was voted out.
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> I imagine this camp is nicer
than your camp.
>> You guys have more space,
I'll say.
But it seems like we've got,
like, more hibiscus and more
coconuts.
What a twist.
The Aitutaki guys have kidnapped
me to come over for the night.
I took it as an honor.
You know, you think I'm a good
competitor, thank you.
>> Are you a good swimmer?
Are you a good...
>> Yeah.
>> You're a good swimmer,
runner, sprinter.
>> They started, like, sweating
me out, asking me all these
questions.
Like, just feeding some nuts,
you know, not hating.
Stuff that really doesn't
matter, I think, in the game.
There are a lot of obstacles
which make it easy and it feeds
a lot of meat in those, a lot of
meat.
I'm always playing the game, so,
you know, just... I've got my
eyes open very much, eyes and
ears, to the tenth.
>> We had to get rid of Cao Boi.
Obviously, that part sucked, you
know?
>> Yeah, I just wish I was clued
in on what was going on, because
now I kind of feel, like,
nervous.
I'd rather be on the same page
and know what's going on than
not.
Just be, you know, clued in.
The vote knocked me off my socks
for a moment.
You know everyone was
blindsiding me by saying, "No,
no, we're going with, you know,
this other plan."
And I just wasn't expecting, you
know, it to be Cao Boi at that
point.
I just don't want it to be me
this next time, so I'm trying to
figure out where people are at.
I totally had voted for
Jonathan, but I'm trying to get
a clue on what's going to happen
next kind of thing.
>> I played my cards right.
I got me some good info right
now.
It was like, "Oh, thanks, more
info."
So I'm going to take my little
notepad and I'm going to go back
to my tribe and let them know
what's going on so that we can
make some moves and really
battle it out.
>> Flicka's going crazy right
now.
She's like, "I want to be in on
the planning with you."
So we need to come up with a
story.
>> The thing I don't like is
that she's been doing it in
front of Nate, right?
>> Like, that whole conversation
happened right in front of Nate.
And I'm like...
>> But we have to know our top
three.
>> To vote off?
>> I feel most comfortable if we
have a third, just because, you
know, within our five we don't
want to just blow up.
>> I mean, I think we should
stay with the same plan, but in
terms of order it would be Ozzy,
Flicka, right, followed by...
>> Who would you rather compete
in individual immunity, Sundra
or Jonathan?
>> Jonathan before Sundra?
>> Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
>> I'm going to go back.
>> Originally the order of
getting voted out was Ozzy would
be next, followed by Flicka,
followed by Sundra, and then it
would be the remaining four.
But we feel like we're starting
to get to the point where a
merge is imminent, so now
there's been talk about, well,
if we come down to it, do we
vote off Jonathan before we vote
off Sundra?
He'd be a tough person to go up
against in an individual
competition.
>> Okay, here we go.
You guys ready?
"Swim, fly, dive, think.
Either way, you are in the
drink.
Browse this catalog and just
pick two.
And they could be yours by the
time you're through."
It's a Survivor catalog!
>> Oh!
>> Page one, check this out.
>> Page one, page one.
>> A collection of oil and
spices.
Sewing kit.
>> The tree mail was awesome.
It was a catalog.
We got to choose two items that
if we win the reward today we
get to have.
>> You guys vote for what you
want to vote for, okay?
It's a democracy.
>> Peanut butter.
>> That's eight votes.
>> I think potatoes.
Do you want bread?
It's ultimately...
>> What right now?
>> What do you want?
>> I'm just being rational.
>> Peanut butter and bread.
>> I want bread, too.
>> You think about, like,
challenges next week, you
definitely need that
carbohydrate.
I had wanted a bag of potatoes
and then peanut butter, trying
to be the voice of reason.
>> Couldn't we just have bread?
>> It won't last as long, but...
>> You could make a peanut
butter sandwich.
>> You can have potatoes with
seafood next week.
>> Three against two, though.
I mean, guys, I don't know...
>> Okay, whatever.
That's fine.
Okay, so put bread.
I was trying to think the
longevity of the tribe, but I've
got to do what the majority
votes, right?
>> PROBST: Aitu, Raro, come on
in!
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Here's how it works.
Each tribe will select three
swimmers and two puzzle makers.
On my "go," the first swimmer
will grab a club, swim out to a
platform, climb to the top, and
then leap off of the platform.
While in midair, you will smash
a plaster box, releasing a key.
You'll then dive down, retrieve
the key, swim back to shore.
You'll continue doing this until
you have retrieved six keys.
Each swimmer must swim out at
least one time.
And each swimmer can only
retrieve one key at a time.
The two puzzle makers will then
use those six keys to open six
locks on a chest.
Inside the chest, puzzle pieces.
First tribe to assemble a puzzle
map of the world wins reward.
Raro, here's what you picked to
play for.
Bread and peanut butter.
Aitu, here's what you picked.
Bag of potatoes and peanut
butter.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Okay, Aitu, you have
to sit three people out.
Who are you sitting out?
Jessica, Sundra, Nate.
So you take Nate to keep him
from competing with Raro, but
you don't trust him to compete
with your tribe.
Is that what I'm reading?
Nate, you'll rejoin your Raro
tribe after this challenge.
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: One more part of the
reward.
In addition, the winning tribe
will choose one member from the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island.
I'll give you a minute to figure
out who your swimmers are going
to be, and we'll get started.
>> I'd rather do puzzle.
I can do puzzles like the back
of my hand.
>> PROBST: All right, the
swimmers for Aitu-- Ozzy,
Candice, and Yul.
The swimmers for Raro-- Rebecca,
Parvati, and Adam.
For reward, survivors ready.
Go!
Ozzy and Rebecca first in the
water.
Ozzy tosses his club.
Not going to bother swimming
with it, throws it out ahead.
Rebecca quickly falling behind.
Big lead for Aitu right off the
bat.
Ozzy smashes the box and the key
drops.
Now he's got to find it.
Rebecca still working her way
toward the platform.
Ozzy has the key and he's
swimming back.
>> Go, Ozzy!
Go, Ozzy!
>> PROBST: Rebecca can hardly
get up on the platform.
>> Ozzy!
>> PROBST: Ozzy back with the
first key.
Yul heads out for Aitu.
Rebecca finally up on the
platform.
Yul swimming out for Aitu.
Rebecca's got to find the key.
Rebecca's heading back without a
key.
>> Come on, Yul!
>> PROBST: Yul at the platform
for Aitu.
Rebecca really struggling in the
water.
Yul has the second key for Aitu.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Yul gaining on
Rebecca.
He's about to lap her.
>> Brad, why aren't you
swimming?
>> Because I'm better at
puzzles.
>> PROBST: Yul back with the
second key.
Candice heading out for Aitu.
Aitu with two keys, Raro no
keys.
>> Pull your top down, baby.
>> PROBST: Rebecca does not have
a key for Raro.
>> Your bathing suit!
>> PROBST: Got to get back to
tag out, Rebecca.
Candice now at the platform for
Aitu.
Rebecca exhausted.
Adam's got a lot of time to make
up.
Adam has to find Rebecca's key
that is in the water somewhere.
>> All right, Candice, let's go,
girl, you got it!
>> PROBST: Adam looking for
Rebecca's key.
Candice now looking for her key.
Adam has the key for Raro.
Candice cannot find her key.
This is a break that Raro needs.
Parvati heading out.
>> I can't find it!
>> Come back!
>> PROBST: Candice heading back
without a key.
It's going to cost them a lot of
time.
Aitu leads two keys to one.
>> There you go!
>> PROBST: And that knocks the
key out.
Candice exhausted.
Ozzy back in the water for Aitu.
Parvati looking for her key.
Ozzy needs to make sure
Candice's key fell out.
>> It's still in the box!
>> Use your fist!
>> PROBST: He doesn't have a
club.
He's going to do it with his
fist.
>> All right!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Parvati has the
second key for Raro.
>> That's what I'm talking
about!
>> PROBST: Ozzy coming back with
the third key for Aitu.
>> Ozzy!
>> PROBST: Aitu now has their
third key.
Yul in the water for Aitu.
Adam back in the water for Raro.
Aitu leads three keys-two.
Yul at the platform.
Adam at the platform for Raro.
Yul cannot find his key for
Aitu.
Adam has the third key for Raro.
Yul has the fourth key for Aitu.
He's heading back.
Raro gaining ground.
>> Good job, Adam!
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Parvati heading out
again.
Yul coming back.
Aitu leads four keys three.
Parvati could make up some time
for Raro.
Parvati has the fourth key for
Raro.
Candice comes up with the key
right away.
Parvati back with the fourth
key.
Adam back in the water for Raro.
Candice out of the water with
the fifth key.
>> You've got this.
>> All right!
>> PROBST: Ozzy heading out for
the sixth and final key.
Adam whacks it, and the key is
in the water.
Adam has the fifth key.
Raro making up ground!
Ozzy smashes the box.
Key is in the water.
Raro has not given up.
Adam back with the fifth key.
Parvati back in water.
Raro with one key left.
Ozzy out of the water with the
final key for Aitu.
>> All right, Ozzy!
>> Yeah, baby, yeah!
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Becky
now have six keys and six locks
to open.
Parvati breaks the box.
The key did not fall!
Becky and Jonathan have the
locks open, opening the chest.
Parvati back up for a second hit
at her box.
Jonathan and Becky not finding
it as easy as they had hoped.
Parvati has the key for Raro.
You've got to keep moving,
Parvati!
Becky excited-- she's figured a
piece of the puzzle out.
>> Don't give up, Parvati.
>> PROBST: Becky's figured out
two pieces.
Suddenly Aitu figuring out the
puzzle.
Parvati back with the final key
for Raro.
Aitu very close.
Aitu wins reward!
Nate, your time with Aitu is
over.
You can head back to Raro.
>> Bye, Nate.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: Aitu, you are sending
one person from Raro to Exile
Island.
Who's it going to be?
>> Adam.
>> PROBST: No hesitation-- Adam.
You've been chosen to go to
Exile Island.
Raro, sadly, I've got nothing
for you.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
Aitu, come get your reward.
>> Candice, go get it.
>> Smooth or crunchy?
>> Smooth.
>> You guys, I'm in love with
everybody that I can see right
now.
If anybody wants a kiss, just
come over here.
I love you.
( laughter )
>> Got to love that.
>> Oh, the sweet taste of peanut
butter.
I mean, I haven't tasted peanut
butter that tasted so good in my
life.
>> Peanut butter kisses for
everybody.
>> I hope that we continue to
grow as a tribe and, you know,
maybe work some things out, and
who knows?
Things just change constantly in
this game, and you never really
know what's going to happen.
>> Right?
>> My team really could have
used me today.
They really could have used me.
For me, it's frustrating because
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't compete.
I'm a good swimmer.
>> The only reason I sat out
because I really felt like we
needed... we kept choking at
the...
>> We needed you swimming,
brother.
>> The thing is, we always choke
at the very end.
And I feel like... I mean,
puzzles... I can... I'm creative
spatial.
I do puzzles.
Like, I get puzzles.
I look at something and I can...
>> I think...
>> But you're right, we did need
a strong...
>> We needed another guy
swimming.
For Brad to take the back seat
today and want to be puzzle boy
when we have a swimming
challenge, pissed me off.
I don't know what his deal was.
Maybe he didn't want to get wet.
Maybe he was cold.
Maybe he's a Nancy boy.
I do not know what he was
thinking, but he did not get his
ass up and swim.
We needed him there.
I don't care about no stupid
puzzle.
"I'm good at puzzles.
I'm real..." I don't care about
that nonsense.
>> He know he's one of our best
swimmers.
He knows that.
He's like, "What's best for the
team."
How hard is it to do a puzzle?
>> That really pissed, me off
because Rebecca was cashed.
I don't know why he insisted on
the puzzle.
I want to punch him in the
mouth.
I'm so angry right now.
I'm like... God, that was
miserable today.
>> Now we've got a storm coming
from Lord knows what.
It's cold.
And I got to come out here and
fish and go back and get wood,
and the girls are burned out, so
I want them to rest.
It's like, thanks for the lovely
way to come home, you know?
>> I'm not happy to be back at
Exile Island.
I am starting to doubt my tribe.
Challenge after challenge, they
just don't come through.
You know, it's hard to soar
like an eagle when you're
surround by turkeys.
>> It hurts to be out here.
The actual rain with the wind,
it kills you.
I was pretty much just in a
fetal position.
I hoped that it would go away.
>> I caught a bird.
>> Wow.
>> What do you guys want to do
with it?
>> Kill it quick, if you're
going to eat it.
It's suffering.
>> It's not suffering.
I'm holding it firmly.
>> You could let it go and it
could go away.
>> Eat it.
>> We should probably eat it.
>> That's why you caught it--
eat it.
>> Yul?
>> Eat it.
>> Yul, get up.
>> I went to go to the bathroom
and it was in the bushes
sleeping.
And I just crept up on it.
>> It's about as big as a
chicken.
All right, I'll pluck it.
>> Good job, man.
Good job, Yul.
Good job, Oz.
>> Good morning!
>> Well, then...
>> All right, good.
Let's... let's respect it and
eat it and enjoy it and get
nourishment from it.
Cool.
>> Ozzy is amazing.
He's like half animal, half man,
you know, part fish, part monkey
part the lord knows what.
>> Will you make me a tree fort?
He's so high up there right now.
>> He's kind of like the little
jungle boy, you know, climbing
these coconut trees and getting
coconuts down, getting fish.
>> Almost the colors of the
rainbow.
>> I mean, coming up with this
bird.
I mean, Ozzy...
( sighs )
...he's just Ozzy.
>> The guy is surprising.
I mean, I underestimated him.
He provides a lot of food, but,
you know, at the same time,
ultimately, we feel that we
should get rid of him while we
still have the control rather
than wait for a merge and
potentially have him dominate
some of the individual
challenges.
>> So what do you think is going
to happen?
>> I have to get my butt in
here.
Okay.
>> We need a plan.
>> What kind of plan?
>> I need to just know what's
happening.
What's going to...
>> I don't know.
I don't...
>> What happens, though, like,
say, okay, we did have to go to
tribal council and we did have
to vote someone out?
>> I don't know.
What do you guys think?
>> Well, the biggest issue, the
number one issue, is none of us
trust Jonathan.
He's just always... the gears
are always turning with him, and
it kind of makes us uneasy.
>> I think that we could
honestly make the strongest
alliance, because you two are
the strongest girls, and I
don't... I don't...
>> Three doesn't make anything.
>> Yeah, but we... I think we
could work it.
>> I don't think... I don't
think... it doesn't work out
when you say it like that, but
if there's two other people,
like Yul and Becky that were
also... or if it was us and
Sundra.
But I just want you to know if
you want to, I mean, you can
trust me.
And if I do end up leaving, if
some strategy works out and I
get voted off, then what are you
guys going to eat?
I think I'm a more valuable
player than Jonathan at this
point.
He can't provide for people.
So if they get rid of me, where
is that going to leave them?
It's going to start getting to
that point where food is going
to become an issue for
everybody.
I might be more of a threat, but
the people that do stick with
me, they're going to be able to
enjoy a ride.
>> PROBST: come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Adam,
returning from Exile Island.
>> How's everyone doing?
Give me a hug.
Come on.
Good to see you.
>> How you doing?
>> PROBST: Adam, I think it's
safe to say you had the worst
night anybody's ever had on
Exile.
>> It was extremely rough there,
Jeff.
>> PROBST: Tell me about the
storm.
We all felt it.
>> It was tough.
I mean, it was raining pretty
hard.
It was hitting me on the back,
it was stinging me.
You know, I was just shivering
all night.
I was in pain.
It was rough.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Yul.
Take back immunity.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, each
tribe will race to arrange a
series of logs from shortest to
tallest as you build a staircase
to the top of the tower.
Three tribe members will sail
down a zipline into the water,
retrieve a bag of puzzle pieces,
swim back to shore.
Then the next person goes.
The three remaining tribe
members will use those pieces to
solve a puzzle.
The first tribe to solve their
puzzle correctly wins immunity,
guaranteed a one in 12 shot at a
million dollars.
Losers, tribal council tonight,
somebody will be voted out.
Aitu, because you have one extra
member, you're sitting somebody
out.
You cannot sit out the same
people in back-to-back
challenges.
Sundra and Jessica sat out the
last challenge.
Who is it going to be this time?
>> I am.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, take a spot
over here.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: I'll give you a few
minutes to strategize, and we'll
get started.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Logs are heavy.
Some people carrying, others
dragging.
Everybody working.
Building a staircase from
shortest to tallest.
Got to figure out the order.
Ozzy and Yul think they have the
tallest log.
>> This one's taller.
>> Why don't you pick it up and
put it next to it?
>> PROBST: Women doing a lot of
the work for Raro.
They're building it from the
bottom up while the guys debate
which is the longest log.
The key is that you put these in
the right order.
You're just making more work.
>> That's it!
>> PROBST: Aitu getting the hang
of it now.
>> That's great.
>> PROBST: The quicker you get
this built, the quicker you get
to the top.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Ozzy puts in the last
log.
Aitu has it.
>> Go, guys!
That's it!
>> PROBST: Once all six to the
top, go!
Yul first down the zipline for
Aitu.
>> Hang on!
>> Help me out.
Help me out.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Yul in the water.
Raro has it!
Raro up the staircase.
Yul has the bag and he's
swimming back.
Got to get up here, Nate.
Go!
Brad, first down the zipline.
Brad into the water.
Brad has his bag.
He's swimming back.
Aitu with a bit of a lead.
>> That throwing is excellent.
>> Let's go, Brad!
>> PROBST: Yul back for Aitu.
Once he's on the mat, go,
Candice!
Candice down the zipline for
Aitu.
Going as fast as she can.
Candice goes deep on the
zipline, drops herself right at
the bag.
Brad's got to get back to the
mat.
Parvati ready to go.
>> Go as far as you can.
>> PROBST: Go!
>> Swing your body.
Swing!
>> PROBST: Parvati getting some
momentum.
She's in a full tuck.
Parvati in the water now.
Parvati has a bag for Raro.
She's swimming back.
Candice swimming back for Aitu.
Aitu still with the lead.
Ozzy ready to go.
Once she hits the mat, go, Ozzy!
Ozzy swinging.
In a monkey pose.
Parvati swimming back.
Let's go, Parvati!
What are you doing walking?
Raro losing more time on the
swimming leg again.
Ozzy swimming like a dolphin as
he makes up time.
>> Come on Pavarti!
Push it Pavarti, push it!
You got it!
>> PROBST: Parvati is back.
Go, Nate.
Nate down the zipline.
Nate imitating Ozzy.
Nate in the water.
He's got the final bag of puzzle
pieces for Raro.
>> Here comes the puzzle!
Go!
>> PROBST: Up the ladder!
>> Come on, Nate.
You're making great time, Nate!
Come on, Nate!
>> You guys are doing great.
Go, Yully!
>> PROBST: Yul back with two
bags of puzzle pieces.
Everybody's got to be up.
Start on the puzzle.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Aitu working on the
puzzle.
Nate coming back for Raro.
>> Be ready!
>> PROBST: Got to climb up the
rope ladder.
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Raro back with the
first bag.
Here's the second bag.
Nate coming up with the third
bag.
Start working on the puzzle.
>> No, this has to be right
here.
>> PROBST: Aitu getting it
together.
Becky, Sundra, Jessica working
well together.
Raro making good progress
quickly.
>> Santa Maria, okay.
>> PROBST: Adam, Jenny, Rebecca,
working well on the puzzle.
We're neck and neck on the
puzzle.
It's going to come down to the
puzzle-building portion of this
challenge.
Immunity on the line.
Raro getting very close.
>> Here, here!
Here!
>> PROBST: Raro wins immunity!
>> PROBST: Raro,
congratulations.
No tribal council tonight,
nobody going home.
Aitu, not good news for you.
Tribal council tonight.
One of you going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp, see you at tribal.
>> You know, it's a tough break.
I mean, what are we going to do?
It's not like they handed us our
asses, you know what I mean?
It's not like the way we beat
them the other day where it was
just ridiculous.
It was just one of those things.
>> Challenge sucked.
We lost.
I feel bummed out that someone
has to go home.
And if it ends up being me that
goes home, that's how it
happens.
But I don't think it's going to
be me.
I think it's going to be
somebody else.
>> So have you thought about who
you would want to vote out if we
end up having to?
>> I don't know.
>> Honestly?
>> No, I don't know.
It's just one of those things
where Jonathan is the biggest
threat for all of us.
>> There's been a debate between
Jessica, Jonathan, and Ozzy who
we should send home first.
You know, Ozzy does bring home a
lot of food, and he does perform
really well in the challenges
for us.
Jessica drives people crazy just
with, you know, the constant
paranoia.
And Jonathan, I think, is kind
of on the cusp in our alliance,
just because from the very
beginning people said they don't
trust him, they're not sure,
blah, blah, blah.
>> She's trying to be
everybody's friend right now,
and I think Jessica is just
covering her ass.
She was like a mosquito that
won't die.
>> Ozzy, he's awesome in
challenges, and I think today,
also, was a very important
indicator, the fact that
Jonathan sat out today.
You know, obviously, we lost,
but at the same time, in, like,
the big picture, we didn't,
like, really need him, per se.
So I thought that was also
brought up by Ozzy, saying that,
you know, if we can all vote
against him in the sense of...
you know, if none of us trust
him, why is he still here?
>> That was the roughest it's
been out there.
Crazy.
Hi.
>> I don't know if you're
feeling the funky vibe in camp,
but we are trying to get the
hell out.
>> Oh, god.
I felt bad.
You know, I mean, it's... it's
the decision, you know?
Do we think it's going to go one
or two more challenges before
the merge?
In which case it might make
sense to keep Ozzy around.
I mean, he really does do well
in the challenges.
You know, there's just no
denying it.
And so maybe... maybe the choice
is Flicka, and we'll just take
our chances in the individuals,
you know?
For all my overthinking, yes, it
my bite me in the butt.
People already think that I'm
thinking too much, playing too
much, or whatever.
I'm trying to choose my battles
carefully.
I'm trying to stay one step
ahead of the competition.
I may trip because I'm running
too far, too fast ahead.
All the girls agree that voting
her off first is better.
I can only play the game as best
I can, make sense to me.
And my feeling always is, if
I've thought of it, somebody
else has thought of it.
>> I know that Jonathan for some
reason seems to inspire some
level of mistrust among pretty
much everybody.
If you talk to anybody,
including other people in our
alliance, they feel like he's a
gamer.
He's here to play hard, and
people don't fully trust him.
And for me, I haven't seen it,
but because everyone else is
suspicious of him, I mean, it
can't help but rub off on me a
little bit.
>> Well, you guys, for what it
is, I thank you for being up
front and honest with everything
today.
As much as it's worth, you know,
even though it's coming down and
nobody really knows what they
want to do, or whatever.
I don't know for sure who is
voting with me for Jonathan.
I would like to say Ozzy is.
I would like it say the girls
are, and Yul, too.
But I think they're just kind of
like, "I don't know what to do,"
because, you know, any of us can
go.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, when we
started this game 18 days ago,
you were divided into groups
based on ethnicity.
Look at this group tonight.
At least one member from all
four of the original ethnic
groups, and yet I don't have any
sense that that plays any part
in this tribe.
Surprise you?
>> No.
I think it's the game
of Survivor.
We're all here to play it.
You divided us into four equal
groups.
We made the connections that we
made.
We were merged into two other
tribes.
And all those connections have
either held or gone away based
on personality, not ethnicity.
>> PROBST: Sundra, is it true
that there's just a natural way
you tend to bond with certain
people and maybe not bond with
others?
>> Absolutely.
You can't plan who you're going
to bond with.
It's nothing calculated or
planned, and there are certain
people, their personalities,
you're just not going to gel.
You can force it, but it's going
to be more work than with
somebody who you just find a
natural chemistry with.
And for those you may not get
along as well with, you try to
find a common ground, you know,
whatever it may be.
>> PROBST: Jessica, let's talk
about who gets along with whom.
>> Just in general, we all get
along with each other.
But, I mean, we all have, like,
friendships, you know, that we
hang out a lot.
I like to go out fishing with
Ozzy and, you know, the girls do
the things in camp.
You know, Jonathan and Yul, they
like to go out clamming.
We all kind of picked our roles
a little bit, but we switched
things up a lot, too.
So I think all of us are capable
of mixing and matching and
having fun.
>> PROBST: Yul, from a strictly
strategic point of view, every
time I've asked Jessica a
question it's been the most
delightful answer with
absolutely nothing said about
how it would impact the game.
>> It's nice to have someone
like that because they're not
going to be a threat.
They're not going to be someone
who's going to be undermining
you, outscheming you, out to get
you or stab you in the back.
So, you know, they're someone
who you can take at face value.
And as long as you can form a
bond with them, they're not
to be someone you're going to
have to watch out for in the
future.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, it's been
brought up a lot that you're a
provider.
Is there a point in the game
where you provide too much,
where you become a threat?
>> God, I hope not.
I hope I can make everyone fat.
I've never been in a position of
being the hunter, and that's
kind of nice to know that I hold
that little bit of
responsibility in my hand.
And, you know, if that ends up
being my demise, then that's
probably the best way that I
could see to go out in this
game.
>> PROBST: Okay, if somebody
does have the hidden immunity
idol, and it turns out you need
to play it, you would present it
to me after the vote.
You would then be immune, and
the person with the next highest
number of votes would be sent
home.
It is time to vote.
Ozzy, you're up.
>> I really admire your spirit,
and I think with another group
of people you would have felt
more comfortable.
Good luck.
>> I didn't trust you before,
and I'm not going to start now.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the vote are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jonathan.
Flicka.
One vote Jessica, one vote
Jonathan.
Jessica.
Two votes Jessica, one vote
Jonathan.
Jessica.
That's three votes Jessica, one
vote Jonathan.
Eighth person voted out of the
Cook Islands, Jessica.
That's four.
That's enough.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, you need to bring
me your torch.
Jessica, the tribe has spoken.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
Well, after 18 days, we have two
tribes, each with six members.
And the big question centers
around momentum.
You think you have it.
I guarantee you Raro thinks they
have it.
Time will tell.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: next time
on Survivor:
>> It's every man for himself.
>> PROBST: Brad loses Raro's
trust.
>> Did just you hear the comment
about it's everyone for himself?
I don't know what's going on
with Brad.
I lost my trust with him.
>> PROBST: But a surprise twist
could change everything.
You have ten seconds to decide
whether or not you want to
change your fate in this game.
>> Oh, my god!
>> It's been an adventure of a
lifetime, and I couldn't have
asked for anything more.
I guess I wasn't playing the
game as hard as I should have,
but it's really hard for me to
change who I am when I just want
to be myself.
Ozzy, good luck.
I'll be rooting for you,
brother.
And memories have been made that
I will never forget, and I'm so
thankful for those experiences.