>> JEFF PROBST: previously on
Survivor...
>> I trust you completely.
>> PROBST: At Raro, Adam and
Candice reconnected.
>> Candice and Adam had a little
attraction, so I'm a little
worried because we don't want
Adam to falter.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
>> North by northeast.
>> Wait, it's north-northwest.
>> PROBST: ...Raro lost their
bearings.
The new Aitu tribe wins their
third challenge in a row!
...and Candice was banished to
Exile Island again.
>> Hopefully this is a
character-building experience.
>> PROBST: At the reward, Aitu
felt like champions.
>> It was a warrior's welcome.
That's part of their culture.
And we were warriors that just
came out of a fierce battle.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
The losing tribe will take back
to camp with them this bottle.
...a message in a bottle
promised a mysterious twist to
the game.
>> Go, Rebecca!
>> PROBST: The two tribes
battled it out...
Sundra has fourth bundle for
Aitu.
...and Aitu was victorious once
again.
Aitu wins immunity!
Raro, we have a date at tribal
council.
You will open this bottle after
the vote.
Back at Raro, Rebecca was blamed
for their loss...
>> There hasn't been one
challenge where Rebecca has been
a strong force to help our tribe
win.
>> PROBST: ...while Jonathan
hoped his hard work earned him a
spot within the tribe.
>> I think I have earned at
least the right of one more
night.
>> PROBST: At tribal...
Tenth person voted out, the
second member of our jury.
...Jonathan was spared.
Rebecca, the tribe has spoken.
Then the mystery of the bottle
was revealed.
>> "You've just voted out one
member of your tribe.
You will now vote out another."
>> PROBST: So Jonathan was back
in the hot seat.
But at the end of the second
vote...
The 11th person voted out of
Cook Islands and the third
member of our jury.
...it was Jenny who took the
fall.
Jenny, the tribe has spoken.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> Fish are already up.
Yep.
You know, I realized the first
time I was out there it was just
like hitting them in a barrel.
And now they're much more
skittish.
Yep.
Well, anyway, I'll bring back a
bunch.
The way the votes came down last
night, they could have gotten
rid of me at any point.
Whether or not that mutiny was a
good idea or not, I can't even
really worry about it.
It worked out my way.
At least at this point, it's
gone the way that I hoped it
would go.
Three people from this tribe
have been eliminated before
Candice and I.
And now I'm in a powerful
position in a smaller tribe, and
that's a good place to be.
>> How's the fire?
>> I'm a little disappointed
this morning.
I know these are young people
who like to sleep in, but
they're going to have to listen
to me now, and they're going to
see my way is a good way.
Let's get this fire going.
>> What's wrong with it?
>> We have to get it together
today, right?
We're going to eat.
Where's the water?
Have we got water?
>> I'll get it right now.
>> Yeah, let's go.
>> I got it.
>> Get fire going, get water
boiling.
We have to hit it right now.
Let's go some firewood going
here.
>> Jonathan better slow his
role.
Don't be coming around barking
no orders in the morning, you
know?
It's like, "Shut up, fool."
Okay, first we all know what
we're doing.
We're not knuckleheads around
here.
>> Damn it.
All that just burned right up.
>> We need to win challenges.
We need to work hard around
camp.
We need to turn things around.
You know, I really got so close
to just bawling them out.
And I almost said, "Either I
have to be your father or your
boss?
Is that how you need to be
treated to do anything in an
organization?
Because I'm not going to lose
because you kids can't get your
asses out of bed."
>> What?
>> I just don't feel good.
>> What's wrong with you?
>> I'm just a little, like,
tired and achy.
>> We've been having challenge
after challenge after challenge,
and not getting a whole lot of
down time to recover, and
yesterday and today I just feel
really crappy.
I am getting a little bit
worried, especially going
forward, that it's going to be a
problem.
>> We are still the underdogs.
I mean, they still have the
numbers over us.
It's like we have to prove
ourselves every day, every
challenge.
That's all we can do.
>> PROBST: Aitu, Raro, come on
in.
Aitu, getting your first look at
the new Raro tribe, Rebecca
voted out at the last tribal
council, and Jenny voted out at
the last tribal council.
>> Two?
Whoa.
>> PROBST: Okay, Aitu, this last
challenge you won is enormous.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Had Aitu lost that
challenge, it would be 7-2.
Sundra, what's the feeling now
as you watch Raro walk in a
tribe of five?
>> Yeah, it's a mixture of
things.
I think we're getting very even,
and it makes you think you can't
get comfortable at any point.
>> PROBST: The game is clearly
up for grabs.
Okay, let's get down to
business.
Paints, brushes, blank tribe
flag...
>> Whoa.
>> ...and new buffs.
You are merging into one tribe.
Drop your buffs.
>> We always wanted to have the
merge before we lost our
numbers, so we were really
hoping it was today, and the
future's looking bright.
>> PROBST: New buff, Ozzy.
Yul, Sundra.
>> "Wow" is the correct word.
Much different game.
We as the Aitu four have some
maneuvering to do.
There are still only four of us.
We're still underdogs.
But winners never quit.
>> PROBST: Now to the big order
of business-- where you're going
to live?
>> We've got more coconuts.
Trust us, get over here.
>> No rats.
>> We have no rats.
>> Jonathan and Candice have
seen both camps.
So what do you guys prefer?
You'd rather stay at Raro?
>> Well, there's definitely more
coconuts.
There are no rats.
>> Leave the ghetto!
>> Come on over, guys.
>> I think we're all cool going
over to their camp.
>> PROBST: So the merge is off
to a good start.
You've decided that you will
live on Raro's beach as one.
Now you have to get to that
beach.
There is a large native
catamaran just off the shore
filled with food and
refreshments.
Follow the drums and have a good
time.
>> Yeah, let's eat!
Yeah, baby!
>> All right!
>> Oh, my god!
>> I knew something was up!
I knew something was up!
>> Thank you!
>> Let's all make a toast.
>> Whoo!
>> Let's all have some fun.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Okay, who wants coleslaw?
>> Hey, you guys have any of
that mustard or barbecue sauce
over there?
Can a brother get a dip?
>> Guys, I know it's all a game,
but I'm really looking forward
to getting to know the people on
the other side I've never gotten
a chance to interact with.
>> He does.
>> We have a new identity now.
We've merged into one tribe.
But the fact of the matter
remains that we're still divided
into two tribes, and as Aitu
came in with lower numbers,
things looked pretty bleak.
We seriously thought it was
going to be over for us.
The fact that we're still here,
it's great.
We're trying to figure out if
there's any chink in the armor
in Rarotonga.
We desperately need to convince
someone to come over to our
side.
>> We're glad to see you.
>> Y'all are some tough
competitors.
>> Let the games begin, one on
one.
It's going to be fun.
>> The Raro kids, all they
wanted to do was get faded,
which is not what we used to
call it.
>> How you doing, brother?
>> I'm starting to do really
well.
>> Oh, no!
There he goes!
>> I'm watching my girlish
figure.
>> These kids are vomiting,
they're eating and drinking so
much.
Is that how you compete in a
competition?
I'm here to win a million... a
million dollars.
That's a one with six zeroes on
the other end of it, okay?
They're psychos.
I mean, I don't understand it!
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you very much!
>> Thank you!
>> Beautiful, lovely.
>> Thank you very much!
>> Thank you!
>> Our new tribe name is
Aitutonga.
We did a little combo with them
both.
so Aitutonga's our new little
snap.
Hey, guys, welcome to our home.
All right, latrines are down to
the east side and west side.
>> We have a coconut grove.
>> I feel we have cool numbers
because we had a 5-4 merge, and
everyone on my previous tribe,
Rarotonga, we're all sticking
together regardless.
Parvati, Adam, and I are very
close.
Jonathan and Candice can't
really sway, because they sold
them out in the mutiny.
So I'm feeling very good.
But it's also good to read the
other tribemates, because
you've got to keep your enemies
close, you know.
>> Yeah.
Tap dance.
>> Yeah, because we're both on
both sides, so...
>> Parvati's gold, got that
lock.
>> So is Sundra.
>> Ozzy is a good captain, you
know?
He's real mellow, down to earth,
homey.
I see Ozzy and I clicking nice.
So I'm keeping my eyes on him in
case things get kind of ugly.
>> Yul and Becky are... they're
solid.
>> Yul is going to get cut
off, though, because my five are
going to want to cut off your
strong points.
>> I've always known that I
might have an ally with Nate,
just from the time when we
kidnapped him over to our side.
I took advantage of that right
away, and as soon as possible,
just started talking to him
about what we could possibly do.
>> Yeah.
>> And then we're straight.
>> I'm so happy about how today
turned out for Raro.
It's a really, really good day.
Adam, don't you dare start with
me.
>> Why?
>> I can tell what's on your
mind.
>> You can read me like a book,
huh?
I've been boozing it up a bit
today.
They had some beer and some
wine, and I... you know, I
partaked a little bit.
>> What happened to Candice?
>> You know, it's good to sit
back and relax, not to have to
worry about challenges, not have
to worry about tribal council.
>> Dirty bird.
>> It's been a great day.
It's been the best day since
I've been here.
>> I'm not sure there is a whole
lot of danger, to be honest.
They don't have the numbers
to arrange a split vote.
Our backs are against the wall.
We need someone to flip.
We've kind of come up with a
desperate plan based on the fact
that I have the hidden immunity
idol, and it could change,
hopefully, the whole flow of the
game.
>> Jonathan I know is... more
than anything else he's a
rational player.
>> Yeah, and I agree.
>> Like, he's going to put
defense above, like, personal
consideration.
I don't know if the other people
here will do that.
>> I agree.
>> Jonathan, if I can convince
him...
>> He's the one person having
the best...
>> Yeah, in a rational sense.
"You know what?
You come over, we have the
numbers, I have the idol, you
can't beat us."
>> It sounds like it might be
the best play to do, then.
>> So let's just talk strategy,
man, going forward.
>> Okay.
Like, does it make sense under
any scenario for us to work
together again?
>> At this point, I could not
entertain what you're talking
about at all.
I do not believe that Ozzy would
trust me.
I'm not sure why you would trust
me.
>> Jonathan deserted us.
We had an alliance going.
And he turned his back on the
alliance and, you know,
basically left us for dead.
But at the same time, like, you
know, I don't really have an
option here.
I've got to figure out something
that's going to work, and this
might work.
>> Let's say I did what you're
proposing, okay, which I'm
actually not entertaining, but
I'll play the scenario.
I don't believe you can get to
the final four unless you're
aligned with the person with the
idol.
Because let's say you have the
idol, okay, and we vote for you,
three of you vote for me, okay.
Boom, I'm out.
Right?
>> Right.
>> So I would have to align with
you, because otherwise I'm going
to get my ass booted out before
the final four.
If I flip again, the Raro people
are going to go mental.
Mental.
Right now, they trust that
there's no way that the Aitu
people would trust me or that I
would ever go back to them.
>> Hypothetically, say I have
the idol, how would I know that
if I were to tell you that I had
the idol you wouldn't just turn
around and tell the rest of your
tribe?
>> Hypothetically, you... we
would have to learn to trust
each other again.
What am I going to say, "I
promise?"
Okay, I promise.
And what's that... what's that
worth to you?
You know what I mean?
I'd have to think long and hard
about my reaction if you even
implied you could show me the
idol.
If you don't have it,
unfortunately, right now, I have
the position where I can say
you're just going to have to sit
and let me figure out what I
want to do.
>> Okay.
All right.
>> All right?
>> To be continued.
>> All right.
>> Always a good thing.
If Yul has the idol, I have to
consider flipping.
I made a very impetuous move
once.
It worked out in my favor.
I have the numbers.
But if I was with the guy who
had the idol all along and I
have to flip back, that's a
fantastic twist.
>> So I think I know a way to
change the game.
>> How?
>> I have the idol.
I found it.
And I think I can use it to get
Jonathan.
>> Yul pulled me aside this
morning and he said that he in
fact has the idol.
He has the hidden immunity idol,
and he's been talking to
Jonathan, trying to convince him
to come to our side.
>> If this works out, all four
of us are in the final four.
>> I mean, how awesome.
We deserve it, right?
Come on!
>> So that was pretty exciting
to hear, because definitely the
nice little wild card, you know?
>> You found it?
That's crazy.
>> I found it.
Like, I wanted to tell you guys,
but then I wanted to wait for a
moment where we could change the
game.
And I feel like this is it.
>> Yul has the idol, and as long
as Yul can convince Jonathan to
flip sides, we're going to be
okay.
The only thing I'm worried about
is what to do with Nate, because
he's a really cool guy, you
know?
I enjoy hanging out with him.
But I still feel like I've got
to be true to Yul and my tribe.
>> This could take all four of
us all the way.
And I'm like, that's how it
should be played.
All right, buddy?
We can do it.
>> What if Ozzy wins immunity?
Yul has to go before Becky and
Sundra.
>> He's really intelligent, and
he's a good competitor.
>> Yeah.
What do you think Nate thinks
about it?
>> I know Nate will do whatever
we wanted.
>> I want Yul gone simply
because I don't like the way he
and Jonathan talk.
>> He's, like, stirring up
trouble.
>> Yeah.
>> He's feeling around, you
know?
>> What is he saying?
>> He's saying "Come over, deal
with us."
And I'm like, "Are you crazy?
Ozzy's going to vote me out in
one second."
>> Who do you think goes first?
>> I mean, that's just stupid.
>> Raro, they want to vote for
Yul right now.
They think he's the mastermind.
But if Yul has the idol, it's
going to be me that goes home,
because they're all going to
vote for me.
Yul will play the idol, I'll
have the second highest number
of votes, and I'm going to get
sent home.
Somebody has the idol, okay?
If it's on our side, then we're
golden.
It doesn't matter.
But I don't have it.
>> Yeah.
>> You don't have it.
If we vote for Yul, and Yul has
it, we're going to find
ourselves going home for no good
reason.
All this is very hypothetical,
because I told Yul, I said,
"Until you show me the idol, I
can't make a decision."
If he doesn't show it to me,
then he's just blowing smoke
( no audio ) ass, and there's no
reason for me to flip.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to your
first individual immunity
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Ozzy, I'll take back the
immunity idol.
Tribal immunity is no more.
Individual immunity is now what
you covet.
This is the immunity necklace.
>> Nice.
>> PROBST: When you have the
immunity necklace around your
neck, you are safe.
You cannot be voted out.
Immunity is the single most
important element in this game.
Ready to get to the challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge is
very simple.
Each of you are going to hang
onto a pole for as long as you
can.
When you fall off the pole,
you're out of the challenge.
Last person left hanging on
their pole wins immunity, is
safe at tonight's tribal
council.
Only one rule-- you cannot use
the top of the pole to support
yourself.
We'll draw for spots, and we'll
get started.
The challenge is officially
underway.
Nate sliding around the pole,
trying to get a foothold.
Adam struggling to hang on.
Candice absolutely calm.
Adam slides down the pole, finds
a safe spot.
Nate loses some ground.
Adam slips a little further down
the pole.
Not much room left.
Adam, first one out of this
challenge.
We are down to eight people
vying for immunity.
>> It's only beginning.
>> PROBST: Where are you feeling
it, Jonathan?
>> My feet a little bit.
My feet are a lot bigger, so the
little bit of rope is... just
hard, I guess.
I don't know.
>> I think Jonathan has a point,
though
>> PROBST: What's that?
>> Basically, the surface area
supporting all of us is about
the same, even if your feet are
a little bit bigger or not.
But, you know, your mass goes up
at a faster rate than surface
area.
It's kind of like why elephants
can't run up trees.
>> PROBST: Just what I was
thinking.
>> Clearly.
>> I'm never going to get a date
again.
>> Smart equals sexy.
>> PROBST: Jonathan loses his
grip, slides halfway down the
pole.
Jonathan now standing on his
last bit of rope.
Nate struggling.
Jonathan curling those toes.
Jonathan, second person out of
the challenge.
First two people out, guys.
Nate starts to slide down the
pole a bit.
Sundra starting to slip.
First woman to lose her
foothold.
Nate down to his last bit of
pole left.
Sundra now on that last bit of
rope.
Not a good sign.
>> Come on, baby.
Come on.
Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Nate, third person
out of this challenge.
We are down to six-- four women,
two guys.
Sundra taking herself back into
the zone.
Yul is adjusting a little,
trying to figure out where he
wants to settle in.
Sundra, fourth person out of
this challenge.
Candice showing off by doing
some squats.
>> You get her on Aitutonga, and
she gets wild.
>> PROBST: Is that your new
tribe name?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: I like it.
Yul trying to dig his hands into
that rope.
Yul starting to slide down even
further.
Yul, the fifth person out of
this challenge.
Ozzy the remaining man, three
women joining him.
Parvati starting to slip.
Rain starting to come in.
Becky slides down.
Parvati now on her last
foothold.
Parvati, sixth person out of
this challenge.
We are down to three -- Ozzy,
Becky, Candice.
Right here, Candice, that's the
piece of jewelry you want.
>> It's pretty.
>> PROBST: Becky, would look
good around your neck.
Ozzy, it's unisex, guys or
girls.
( laughter )
>> I like it.
>> Becky!
>> PROBST: Becky's feet give out
suddenly.
Becky is the seventh person out
of the challenge.
We are down to the final two,
Ozzy and Candice.
Both obviously, want this
immunity quite a bit.
Rain starting to really pick up.
Nate liking it.
>> Rain, rain!
>> PROBST: You think the rain's
going to hurry this up?
>> We could be out here until
tomorrow morning with these two.
I love you, Ozzy, I love you,
Candice.
>> PROBST: Candice makes the
first move, sliding down the
pole.
The first move she's made in
over two hours.
Candice sliding down a little
further.
Candice now on the last rope
foothold.
Candice, drops out.
Ozzy wins the first individual
immunity!
>> PROBST: Ozzy, come on over.
>> I feel like an old man.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
You are safe at tonight's vote.
One of you going home tonight.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
See you at tribal.
>> Yeah.
>> You did amazing.
I can't believe that you stayed
up so long.
>> I was like, "This is my only
chance.
I've got to take it."
>> After the first hour I was,
like...
>> I'm happy Ozzy got the
immunity necklace, because I
respect him as a competitor.
You know, at least he's safe for
another couple of days because I
like the captain.
If there's a way I can work with
him, I'm definitely down.
>> How much longer would you
have stayed up there?
>> I think I could have kept
going.
>> Yeah.
>> Ozzy, him winning the
challenge today, is a perfect
example of why we should get rid
of him as soon as possible.
He's the biggest threat.
But right now he's got immunity.
So tonight our tribe is sticking
together, and we're going to all
vote out Yul.
>> Yul, you were on there for a
while.
>> Yul is the choice because
he's brilliant.
He's, like, Mr. Harvard-Yale-
Stanford guy.
And he's also really, really
strong.
So we just want to get him out
as quickly as possible.
>> I got eight.
>> So the hypothetical is a
reality.
And I'm asking you for both of
our sakes to become my ally
again.
>> I was not that surprised when
Yul showed me the idol.
After our conversation yesterday
it made perfect sense.
So now I have a lot to think
about and a huge decision to
make, because basically, Yul
said, "Vote with us or you're
going home tonight."
>> This is only chance we've
got.
Everyone recognizes that.
This is the only way this is
going to work.
I thought about it, though.
I would want to go to the final
two with you, because, honestly,
I think my chances against you
are better than either Becky or
Sundra.
>> I appreciate you showing that
to me.
I have to think about it.
I really do.
>> All right.
>> Okay?
>> To be continued.
>> My only concern about Yul is
he's the only other guy who has
been to exile.
Do you have the idol?
>> Yul was there for, like, a
day.
There's no way he has it.
>> I floated this idea to them.
I said, "What if Yul has the
idol?"
Well, they were like, "He
doesn't have it.
He's got to go."
These people aren't thinking.
I don't believe they're smart
enough.
They don't want to put the
mental energy into even running
the scenario of what if Yul
actually has it?
And if I can't convince them,
Yul will play the idol, it will
bounce back, and I'll be going
home very early.
>> Yeah!
>> Jonathan refuses to vote Yul
off.
>> No, he can't come into our
game and tell us what to do, you
know what I'm saying, dog?
You and I are calling the shots,
dog.
>> I know, but we need five
votes.
>> Okay.
I mean, I agree, I just...
You know what I'm saying?
>> Nate's convinced we should
get rid of Yul, and I'm fine
with that, but I'm concerned
about Nate, just because he's
acting different recently.
He's not his usual self, and
he's been hanging around Ozzy a
lot, and that concerns me.
>> Nate just needs to chill out.
>> He's just thinking too much.
>> We're good.
And Jonathan's good.
>> Please understand, I have to
think about this.
It's an extraordinarily big
thing to do.
It's very appealing to jump over
to them.
On the other hand, Adam and
Candice welcomed me to this
tribe, really helped me out,
kept me alive here.
I would hate to betray them,
because if I do that, it makes
me the guy who betrayed every
single person in the game at one
time or another.
Basically, Yul said, "We'll pick
whoever you want to go."
And since I feel some loyalty to
Adam, I said Nate, who I trust
the least, because I know him
the least.
>> You guys have to think about
that.
>> It's entirely possible that
Jonathan's pretending to go
along with the plan in order to
direct the vote away from him
onto Nate.
And if he doesn't vote with us
tonight, I'm going to play the
idol, and once it's played, then
I'm vulnerable.
I don't want to do that.
So I don't know.
I'm hoping somehow all this
clicks together.
>> Either way, people are going
to be pissed.
Either I'll have betrayed the
Raro people and I'm a complete
bastard, or I didn't jump over
to the Aitu people, and I'm a
complete bastard who screwed
them twice.
I don't know what I'm going to
do.
I wish I knew.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury.
Brad, Rebecca, and Jenny, both
voted out at the last tribal
council.
Jonathan, how did the merge
change this game?
>> Well, the very least of it is
the sleeping accommodations have
been hard.
There's nine in a tent, and
we've all had to get used to
living together after so many
weeks of vying with each other
like this.
>> PROBST: Sundra, how did the
game change from your
perspective?
>> Well, the game changed in
that we have to start thinking
individually as well as still
thinking within your alliances,
your former tribemates.
There's a lot of time with...
with these people, so you can't
help but be bonded.
>> PROBST: Nate, tribal lines
still in play?
>> Yeah.
Oh, definitely.
It's like we've all made it to a
certain point.
But, kind of, we're kind of
starting all over, so you're
going to definitely stick to
what you're comfortable with,
and those who know you, and
those who you know.
>> PROBST: Yul, so if that's the
case, then Aitu is down in
numbers.
>> The likelihood that all four
of us are here at all is very
low, but we stuck together, and
prevailed against the odds.
But the fact remains, you know,
both tribes are tight, and so we
came in at a huge disadvantage,
and the odds are still stacked
against us.
So I don't know what our fate is
going to be.
I feel like tonight is going to
be pivotal.
>> PROBST: Becky, do you see any
bonds, people that are closer
maybe than you'd like them to
be?
>> I definitely felt bonds
between those two.
And they're very close, just
body language.
So when he came over here, we
sort of saw that.
>> The closest bond out here is
those two right now.
>> Becky, you and Yul, y'all
come on!
You trippin'.
>> But it was different.
I don't want lie on his lap.
It's just a different bond,
different body language.
>> PROBST: Parvati, what's going
on between Adam and Candice?
>> They love each other.
They want to make babies.
They snuggle next to each other
in the shelter.
I got booted out of my spot.
>> You told me you left because
he wasn't snugly, he wasn't
paying enough attention to you.
>> There are two sides of me.
I mean, they can both snuggle up
with me if they like.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, does it
concern you a little bit to see
two people pairing up in a way
that's different than you and
Ozzy might become friends?
>> Ah!
>> Certainly different than me
and Ozzy.
I think they really are enjoying
each other's company, but,
honestly, I do not see that it
has moved into some kind of
romantic situation.
And to answer, no, it doesn't
concern me.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, how will this
game be different after
tonight's vote?
>> I think this will definitely
set something in motion.
You know, either it's going to
just go downhill for Aitu, or,
you know, something crazy could
happen.
At this point, I think we're
definitely at a pivotal moment.
>> PROBST: Nate, do you think
the dynamic will be different
when you guys go back to camp
tonight?
>> Yeah, it's definitely going
to stir up the waters.
If someone from Raro decided to
jump over, the cat's going to be
out of the bag.
Or if someone from Aitu...
because pretty much both tribes
are sticking together.
Let's keep it real, you know?
Like, it's kind of tribe against
tribe.
So if there's a leak, definitely
the mood's going to flip.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, how has
this game changed you as a
person?
>> I have enjoyed every second
of it.
I've bonded with people younger
than me in a way that I haven't
in years.
I have tried to drink in every
minute of it, because I know
that I will never have an
experience like this again.
And it has been a profound and
wonderful experience for me.
>> PROBST: Let's get to the
business of the vote.
Ozzy has the immunity necklace.
If you want to give it to
somebody else, you can.
>> Ah...
( laughter )
>> PROBST: And if somebody has
the hidden immunity idol and it
turns out you need to play it
tonight, you would present it to
me after the vote.
You too, would be immune, and
the person with the next highest
number of votes would be gone.
It is time to vote.
Sundra, you're up.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Yul.
Yul.
Two votes Yul.
Nate.
Two votes Yul, one vote Nate.
Yul.
Three votes Yul, one vote Nate.
Nate.
Three votes Yul, two votes Nate.
That's three votes Yul, three
votes Nate.
Yul.
Four votes Yul, three votes
Nate.
We're tied.
Four votes Yul, four votes Nate,
one vote left.
12th person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury...
Nate.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, Nate, you need to
bring me your torch.
Nate, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> One love.
>> PROBST: Well, there was a lot
of talk tonight about how
pivotal tonight's vote was.
And judging from Nate's reaction
and the looks on many of your
faces, I'd say the impact was
significant.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: next time
on Survivor:
>> It's vile to me.
>> PROBST: Jonathan's betrayal
sends the tribe reeling.
>> It pissed everyone in this
game off.
>> Are they eating?
>> PROBST: And lines are drawn.
>> Since when do you guys not
share?
That's so rude.
You're trying to weasel your way
in.
>> How dare you?
>> And all these people have
said that they don't like you.
>> That's bollocks and you know
it.
>> It hurts to leave this early
in the game.
Jonathan, kiss my ass.
You are a dirty, stanky, wack
fruitcake who sold me out and
sold out our tribe when we
brought you in, you trading
bastard.
So kiss my ass, Jonathan.
Other than, everyone I love.
But that's how it's get to be in
this world.