>> JEFF PROBST: previously on
Survivor...
>> I'd rather be on the same
page and know what's going on.
>> PROBST: Aitu was uneasy with
their kidnapped Raro member in
camp.
>> He's going crazy right now.
>> The thing I don't like is
that that whole conversation
happened right in front of Nate.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
Rebecca quickly falling behind.
...Aitu forced Nate to sit out.
>> Brad, why aren't you
swimming?
>> Because I'm better at
puzzles.
>> PROBST: Nate watched
helplessly as his Raro tribe
fell behind and never recovered.
Aitu wins reward!
When Nate returned to Raro...
>> He knows he's one of our best
swimmers.
>> PROBST: ...the tribe
questioned Brad's decision not
to swim.
>> We're always choking at
the...
>> We need you swimming,
brother.
>> The thing is, I'm creative
spatial.
I do puzzles.
>> Brad pissed me off.
"I'm good at puzzles."
I don't care about that
nonsense.
>> PROBST: At Aitu...
>> I caught a bird.
>> PROBST: ...Ozzy's role as
provider was a mixed blessing.
>> Good job, Oz.
I underestimated him.
We should get rid of him while
we still have the control rather
than wait for a merge and
potentially have him dominate
some of the individual
challenges.
>> PROBST: Go, Nate!
At the immunity challenge, Raro
made a comeback.
Raro wins immunity!
Aitu, tribal council tonight,
one of you going home.
See you at tribal.
>> That's the decision.
>> PROBST: Back at Aitu,
Jonathan targeted Flicka.
>> Maybe the choice is Flicka.
I'm trying to stay one step
ahead of the competition.
>> PROBST: While Flicka tried to
target Jonathan.
>> PROBST: But her scrambling
pestered some of the girls.
>> She was like a mosquito that
won't die.
>> PROBST: And Ozzy, who was
concerned about his own
vulnerability, agreed that
Jonathan was a threat.
>> Jonathan seems to inspire
some level of mistrust among
pretty much everybody.
I haven't seen it, but because
everyone else was suspicious of
him, I mean, it can't help but
rub off on me a little bit.
>> PROBST: In the end...
Eighth person voted out of
the Cook Islands...
...Flicka's scrambling became
her downfall, and she was voted
out.
Jessica, the tribe has spoken.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> Listen, we're in a good
place, right?
We've really done well, the five
of us.
>> We need to stay tight.
>> And we'll continue to stay
tight.
We know what the next move is if
we have an elimination, right?
The most solid thing is if we go
in with six, and they have four,
and we keep Ozzy around for at
least one vote, vote somebody
off, then vote Ozzy off, and the
five of us can,, you know, go to
town.
People are a little antsy as
we're approaching what we think
is a merge in the next couple
of days.
We have five strong now.
I assume if there's one more
immunity challenge and we lose
it, we will let go of Ozzy.
But I don't care how tight you
think your fivesome is, things
are going to change.
>> You know, anything can happen
at this point.
>> I don't want to keep this six
through the merge.
I want to get back together with
Adam and Parvati.
So I'm just ready for some
movement, get some other people
out of here.
I'm nervous because it's kind of
like the calm before the storm,
you know.
I think stuff's about to start
moving.
>> As much as everybody's
saying, "Let's stay together
with the six," it's going to get
to a point where somebody's
going to get greedy, you know
what I mean?
And it's going to get ugly.
And I don't, you know....
>> I don't want them to do it to
me.
>> Right.
I don't want to be the one left
out to dry.
>> You and I are tight.
We're going to make this work.
Set something up with Parvati.
Let's hope we can do that.
Maybe it'll be us four
Caucasians in the final four--
me, you, Adam, Parvati-- and at
that point, we have the numbers.
And I just think we have to be
the ones to make that flop
before they do.
I am determined to not be the
guy who made the move too late,
you know?
I've trusted you all along, you
trusted me.
And it's gotten us a long way,
and it's going to get us a long
way further.
Candice and I talked a lot about
the fact that eventually we were
going to have to do some kind of
flop.
She's the one person that I'm
the tightest with.
Only two people can sit at the
final two, and I want it to be
you and me, I swear to God.
>> Jonathan's got this new plan,
but I'm not sure that Jonathan
has really any allegiance.
I think he'll do whatever he
needs to get by, so I'd like to
see Jonathan go.
>> Do you think we could merge
now?
>> We're going to merge soon.
>> Did you just hear that
comment about, "It's everyone
for themselves"?
>> I have to play Brad right
now.
He has done questionable things,
you know?
He's Slim Shady right now,
straight-up.
>> That infuriates me that he
said that.
It's not an individual game yet.
>> We have to play for our team.
>> No.
>> I lost my trust with him, and
it sucks, because I like the guy
a lot.
There's still team.
There's no "I" in that team
right now for him.
And so I'll make him think,
"Yeah, dog, I got your back,
homey.
Yeah, we tight."
Sucker.
>> PROBST: Raro, come on in.
Aitu, come on in.
Raro getting your first look at
the new Aitu tribe.
Jessica voted out at the last
tribal council.
Okay, before we get to today's
reward challenge, we're going to
do something a little different.
I'm offering each of you the
opportunity to mutiny and join
the other tribe.
>> Man!
>> Oh, my god!
>> PROBST: You have ten seconds
to decide whether or not you
want to change things up and
maybe change your fate in this
game.
If you want to move, step off
your mat and join the other
tribe.
The clock is ticking.
Five, four, three, two.
Candice is mutinying.
One.
Jonathan mutinies at the last
second.
That is it.
Jonathan, Candice, you're Aitu
no more.
Join Rarotonga.
>> Hi.
>> Welcome back.
>> PROBST: Candice you're now a
member of Raro, Jonathan, a
member of Raro.
So, Aitu, you just had two
members of your tribe mutiny.
Yul, you don't look happy.
>> No, I'm stunned.
I thought we had a pretty good
game plan, and I'm very
surprised.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, what's your
reaction?
>> It doesn't really surprise
me.
They don't have the backbone to
stick with their tribe, then
that's fine.
I'm sure that they're going to
get their fate sooner or later.
>> PROBST: Okay, everybody ready
to get to today's reward
challenge?
Two of you from each tribe will
start inside a barrel.
On my "go," the rest of the
tribe will push you through a
series of obstacles.
Along the way, you'll collect a
total of four buoys which you'll
then use to float the two people
in the barrel across the lagoon.
When you reach the center of the
lagoon, dive down and retrieve
four flags.
When you reach the other side of
the lagoon, you'll take those
four flags and attach them to a
flagpole.
The entire tribe will then dig
down, uncover an ax, use that ax
to chop a rope which will raise
your flags.
The first tribe to raise their
flags wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The winning tribe
will go to a nice, relaxing
environment.
You'll have coffee, some
muffins.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Danishes.
>> Oh, my god!
>> PROBST: And because it's
always nice to have something to
read with your morning cup of
coffee, you will have letters
from home written by your loved
ones for you.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: This is going to be
two women and two men from each
tribe.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize.
In the barrel for Aitu, it is
Becky and Sundra.
For Raro, Jenny and Candice.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Both barrels heading down, a
quick ride into the sand.
Ozzy gets the buoys for Aitu!
Adam and Nate get the buoys for
Raro!
Ozzy back first.
Yul and Ozzy putting the buoys
in the barrel.
Nate and Adam back with their
buoys loading in the barrel.
Aitu off and running.
Raro right behind.
Aitu with the lead as they get
to the log roll.
You've got to roll them over
these logs.
Not going to be a comfortable
ride.
>> PROBST: Aitu still with a bit
of a lead.
Nate and Adam right behind.
Once you hit your mat, you can
get your next two buoys.
Aitu on the mat!
Raro's on the mat.
Ozzy back with the buoys for
Aitu.
Nate and Adam back with the
buoys for Raro.
Two new tribes battling it out.
Who made the right move?
Who made the wrong move?
Candace and Jenny suffocating
with all the buoys inside.
Got to get those buoys clipped
to the barrels so you can float
across the lagoon.
Ozzy and Yul in the water.
Raro still struggling.
They've got to get in deeper
water.
Aitu is now floating their
barrel.
Raro now in the deep enough
water.
They can start floating, but
Aitu has a big lead at this
point.
Aitu has reached their flag.
Ozzy's got the first flag.
Raro cannot get there.
Ozzy up with the second flag.
Raro is floating away.
Ozzy comes up with his final two
flags.
He's got all four.
Raro cannot fight the current.
Let's go!
Raro, no chance of getting back.
Aitu now on the other side.
Ozzy and Yul have been
workhorses on this challenge.
>> Get out, get out!
>> PROBST: big reward on the
line.
Somebody going to Exile Island.
Becky's going to hang the flags.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Aitu has their four
flags.
Now they've got to find the ax.
They've found the ax.
Aitu wins reward!
>> Yes!
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
>> PROBST: Well, it would be an
understatement to say that this
game has just taken a dramatic
turn.
Aitu, as winners, you are
sending somebody from the Raro
tribe to Exile Island.
>> Hmm...
>> PROBST: who's it going to be?
>> Candice.
>> PROBST: Candice, big signal
coming from your old tribe.
Let's go, Candice.
Raro, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head on back to camp.
Sundra, you're crying.
>> Because, you know, I wanted
to stay true to my guys, and we
worked well together.
Feels good.
>> PROBST: Well, in this case,
it certainly paid off to stick
together.
You have a big reward-- coffee,
tasty assortment of pastries,
love letters from home just
behind you.
Grab your stuff.
Head on over.
>> Whoo!
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, my god!
>> I love you guys!
>> Yeah, I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
>> Me, too.
I don't know when I've felt like
this.
When I saw the mutiny in its
completion, the numbers were
scary.
Standing there and you're
feeling so small and pitiful and
you look over to the Raro side,
and they look so big and
triumphant.
And when we won the challenge, I
cried.
I straight up cried.
I don't think I've ever been as
happy in my life.
>> All right, let's have a
toast, guys.
>> To Aitu.
>> Working together, keeping
calm, cool, collected.
>> This will take us to the end,
guys.
>> Cheers.
>> Oh, the reward was beautiful.
We had these dry robes that we
could put on.
And then laid out before us was
every kind of pastry you can
think of.
It was like a recharge, you
know?
I feel, like, brand new.
I feel like I'm ready to do
anything.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Who is it?
>> That's you?
Oh, you were so cute!
>> Oh, sexy Becky.
I love it.
>> That's my son.
>> Oh, my god, he's adorable.
>> Okay, I like this one.
>> All right...
>> No, we're seeing these.
>> I'm feeling really good about
my tribe.
When you see each other's
families and see pictures of
each other growing up, I mean,
it just really hits you that
these are real people that
you're interacting with, you
know-- people that with hopes,
dreams, fears, aspirations.
>> I haven't seen my son in
three weeks, and in the letter,
he was like, "I hope you're
fine."
And he said that he was really
concerned that I'm not alone.
I have a great little boy, and
I'm realizing, "What the hell am
I doing here?"
But I always teach my son
"Winners never quit, and
quitters never win," so I can't
teach him that and come out here
and quit.
>> That's Ozzy.
>> Ozzy needs a hug.
>> Aww...
>> We are stronger than we've
ever been.
The mutiny solidified our
commitment and dedication to
each other.
I mean, we're a team to the end
now.
>> Oh, there's nothing in here.
I've been waiting the whole time
to get back with my friends Adam
and Parvati.
So I made the decision to
mutiny.
You know, it's four people on
the old Aitu tribe that are
really mad at me right now.
Obviously they're going to have
it out for me.
I was surprised that Jonathan
stepped out right behind me.
He's been saying that we were
really, really close, and we've
been tight the whole time, but I
haven't really trusted Jonathan
to begin with.
Now I'm here, sitting on Exile
Island by myself, while Jonathan
is bonding, having a good time,
and I'm out of the game.
>> Wow, here I am.
>> You're back.
>> I took a step into the
unknown, guys.
I wanted to be here and meet
some of you folks.
So were you guys totally
shocked...
>> I was.
>> ...at Candice and I wanting
to come over here?
>> No.
>> No?
Good.
>> What?
>> I mean, it's a crazy thing to
do.
And Candice and I are the last
two in here.
I don't know how tight you guys
are, but it seemed like the
right thing to do, you know.
If I've made a mistake it was in
trusting Candice too much, and
she made an impulsive move and I
followed her.
So I'm in the danger seat now.
I'm the eighth man in.
I consider myself a loyal
person, and Candice and I have
been together through the whole
thing.
You know, I saw her do it and I
said, "Okay, let's go."
My game plan is to earn their
trust, and the only way I can do
that right now is by being
totally non-threatening and
anxious to help.
And listen, I hope it doesn't
bite me in the butt, but...
>> Welcome.
>> Thank you.
>> I knew Candice was going to
come over, but my man Jonathan
rolled over too with her.
You must be smoking some good
stuff if you think you're going
to roll up into our crib and
just start stirring waters, you
know?
Brad is going to be safe for a
vote if it has to come to that,
you know?
Because he at least stood with
us and said, "I'm not budging."
So the first one, definitely, is
Jonathan.
There was no question about
that.
To really think we all have your
back after we just saw you sell
out your other tribe?
Are you dumb?
>> You're good around camp.
You're a workhorse.
>> I'm out here to do this, you
know?
We could get voted off tomorrow.
I don't know what's going to
happen.
>> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
Sometimes opportunity knocks,
you've got to just walk through
the door and hope for the best.
So for me and Candice, the risky
time is the next two votes.
>> I know.
>> Listen, I don't know what's
going on over here.
>> Yeah.
>> Just so you know, she and I
wanted to come back and deal
with you and Parvati.
>> Yeah, I know.
I understand that, I understand
that.
>> You know what I mean?
>> That's cool with me.
I'll do that.
Because we're the original
tribe, man.
Jonathan really wants myself,
him, Candice, and Parvati to be
the final four.
You know, just to have someone
there that wants that and wants
to include me is good to have
along the ride.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Candice,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Hey, guys.
>> Hey!
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first.
Let's take back immunity.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
paddle out in glass-bottom boats
searching for three underwater
targets.
When you line up the crosshairs
on your target with the
crosshairs on your boat, you'll
release a cannonball, which will
drop from the boat, hitting a
target, releasing a pair of
buoys.
When you have all the buoys back
to shore, use the buoys to solve
a word puzzle.
One buoy provides a clue.
The rest of the buoys will form
the one-word answer.
First tribe to solve it
correctly wins immunity,
guaranteed a one in 11 shot at a
million bucks.
Losers go to tribal council
tonight.
Somebody will be voted out.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Raro, you have four
extra members.
You cannot sit out the same
people in back-to-back
challenges, so your decision is
made.
The people who participated
yesterday will sit out today.
Take your spots, we'll get
started.
All right, for Raro it's
Parvati, Jonathan, Rebecca, and
Brad taking on Becky, Ozzy, Yul,
and Sundra for Aitu.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You're looking for three targets
releasing three pairs of buoys.
Both tribes pushing their boats
as far as they can.
>> Get in, Yul.
>> PROBST: Aitu first to start
paddling.
Raro is paddling.
Raro immediately off the course.
>> Turn, turn, left.
>> I see the first one over
here.
I see the first one over here.
>> Okay.
>> All right, slow down, slow
down.
>> Okay.
>> Backpedal, backpedal.
>> PROBST: Aitu trying to line
up their first target.
>> Okay, tell me whenever you're
ready.
One, two... drop it.
Do it!
>> PROBST: Aitu releases a
cannonball.
>> We were right on it.
>> PROBST: Just off.
>> Over here, straight!
>> PROBST: Both tribes searching
for that first set of buoys.
Raro very close to their buoys.
>> You guys ready?
>> PROBST: Brad and Parvati
trying to line it up.
>> Okay.
>> Drop, drop, drop, drop!
>> PROBST: Jonathan releases a
cannonball for Raro.
>> Backwards.
Straight back.
>> PROBST: Misses the target.
>> Backpedal a little bit, just
a little.
>> PROBST: Aitu, can they get
the crosshairs lined up?
>> Just a little bit, drop!
>> PROBST: No luck.
This challenge demands that you
work together well.
>> Brad, paddle a little bit on
your side.
>> PROBST: Raro easing into
it...
>> Okay, a little bit more.
>> PROBST: ...gently.
>> Now.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Raro has the first
pair of buoys.
>> My god!
>> Nice, guys!
>> Here we go-- one, two, three,
drop.
>> PROBST: Aitu misses again.
>> Here we go.
>> It's right in front of us.
>> Here it comes, here it comes.
>> PROBST: Raro taking a shot at
their second set of buoys.
>> Wait.
>> Okay, ready?
>> Drop!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Raro releases their
second set of buoys.
Raro now leads two sets of buoys
to none for Aitu.
>> Right there.
>> PROBST: Aitu very close to
their buoys.
>> Should I just go for it?
>> No.
>> I think I got it.
I got it!
See?
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> PROBST: Aitu releases their
first set of buoys.
Raro heading to their final set
of buoys...
>> Okay, wait.
All right, we're going to have
to backpedal.
>> PROBST: ...and drifting off
course.
>> Just keep doing what we're
doing.
We're doing good.
>> PROBST: Aitu trying to get
their second set of buoys.
>> We're very close.
Okay.
Okay, yes.
Yes, we're... try it.
>> PROBST: Aitu misses again.
>> Through here.
>> Hold on, hold on, hold on.
He sees it.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Aitu connects with
their second set of buoys.
We are now tied, two sets each.
>> I can spot the thing through
the...
>> Shhh!
>> PROBST: Both tribes now with
one target left.
>> All right, all right, let's
get the last one, guys.
>> And go, go, go!
>> Release again, release!
Backwards.
We missed it.
>> PROBST: Raro misses again.
>> We're going to lose all
our...
>> Raro just wasted a
cannonball.
They weren't paying attention.
>> Oh, please, Jeff.
>> PROBST: What's that?
>> I said, oh, please!
>> PROBST: Jonathan getting
frustrated by me.
Day 21.
>> We're going to drift over it.
>> PROBST: Aitu sees their
target.
>> Yeah!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Aitu takes a shot and
releases their third set of
buoys.
Aitu now has all three sets.
They can begin paddling back to
shore.
Raro still right on top of their
third set of buoys.
Going after another shot.
>> I got it!
>> PROBST: Aitu has all their
buoys.
They're paddling back to shore.
Raro not giving up!
Got to hit that third target!
>> Now!
>> We blew it!
>> Did it drop?
>> All right, we're on the mat.
>> PROBST: Aitu back to the mat.
Got to get all their buoys back
to the big mat.
>> Let's go!
>> Jonathan, paddle forward.
Don't watch them.
Look at what we're doing.
>> All right, this says "The
most famous mutiny in history
occurred aboard this ship."
>> PROBST: Aitu working to get
this puzzle together.
Bounty.
Aitu wins immunity!
>> Yeah!
>> Are you kidding me?
>> Son of a...
>> PROBST: Well, Aitu, another
big win today.
Immunity, no tribal council,
nobody going home.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: On the other side of
the coin, Raro, two big losses.
Tribal council tonight.
Somebody from this tribe will be
voted out of this game.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
I'll see you at tribal.
>> I'm so bummed out.
>> So sorry, guys.
>> Goodness, gracious, that was
stupid.
>> I saw you say that...
>> I'm a little hungry, but it
was...
>> Well, luckily, you were only
out there one night and it
wasn't raining, right?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> I'm happy to have Candice
back from Exile Island.
It takes a little bit of the
onus off of me being the only
new guy.
They can see who the two of us
are, and she and I have trusted
each other.
>> Not tight.
>> Not tight?
Not too tight?
>> No.
>> Okay, good.
>> Not too tight at all.
I was shocked.
He had, like, long talks with
Yul all the time.
And he only really came back and
tried to, like, solidify
something with me in the past
few days.
He's just doing whatever is best
for him and, like, working
everybody at the same time, you
know what I mean?
>> What's up?
>> Jonathan, AKA "Lord Knows
What He's Thinking Knucklehead,"
to leave his tribe, is working
very hard around here.
So right now, we're going to do
away with Brad, because we're
scared if we go to a merge, he's
going to go with Becky and Yul.
I've got to put a Denzel on
today and play Brad like it's
all good, you know, like, keep
him in the loop.
He thinks I'm out to cut up
Jonathan, so I'm going to let
him think he's safe.
( yawns )
What's up, brother?
>> What's up?
Were you sleeping?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Who?
>> Okay, that's fine.
>> Candice informed me that
Jonathan's been running his
mouth a little bit, just talking
trash, which I think is funny
because now he's kissing my butt
along with everybody else's butt
in our tribe.
So he can just kiss our butts,
and we'll go ahead and vote him
off after that.
>> I want to get rid of that
kid.
I mean, now he's kissing
everyone's butt after that.
>> I told you, man, he's a punk-
ass...
>> I know he is.
He's a punk.
But, I mean, we can't switch
now.
I'm going to beat his ass.
>> He's a punk.
>> My man Adam wants to take a
brick and beat Jonathan in the
head with it.
>> You know, I told you I
smelled dookie, dog.
>> Pisses me off.
>> But we've got to think smart.
Game's not over yet, so it's a
fair playing ground.
>> PROBST: Looks like it's going
to be a wet night.
So let's talk about the mutiny.
Brad, when you saw Candice step
off the mat, followed right
behind by Jonathan, what was
your initial thought?
>> My initial thought was, "Wow,
that is one gutsy girl."
I mean, here she has four people
now vying against her.
>> PROBST: Jenny, is there a
part of you thinking, "Well, you
know what, that's okay"?
They're at the bottom of the
totem pole.
They need to know that.
>> Even though they're on the
bottom of the totem pole we have
an advantage compared to the
Aitu.
And if we merge, we're just
going to pick them off like
zits.
I've been hanging around Nate
too long.
>> PROBST: Candice, are you okay
with the fact that this tribe
comes to tribal council, where
somebody is going to be voted
out, and there's joking and
laughter?
>> I think that's the great
thing about this tribe, and it's
one of the reasons I stepped out
on the mat.
I felt like this tribe has a
good time.
>> PROBST: So you're telling me,
Candice, that you stepped off
that mat because you could just
sense that Raro was just a lot
more fun?
>> I didn't say that was the
only reason.
That's one of the reasons.
I mean, they win when it counts.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, are you a
little bit concerned that "I
could be an easy guy to get rid
of?"
Because they didn't invite you
over.
You were given the opportunity
to just join them.
>> Of course I'm concerned, you
know?
I was the last guy off the mat.
Maybe it was a second later.
But yes, you know, somebody's
going to go home tonight, and
I'd be silly if I didn't think
it could be me.
>> PROBST: Nate, what's your
take on this unit right now as a
tribe, or as a family, whatever
you want to call it?
>> My six I had yesterday before
mutiny, I was all good with.
The other two coming in, Candice
and Jonathan, they seem very
nice, so, you know, we're still
adapting to them.
I can't really give you a fair,
honest answer about them because
I'm still reading them.
>> PROBST: What would be the
concern about Candice?
>> Oh, the girls may find her as
a threat because she's pretty
lethal-- the only female who has
ever been to exile, and, you
know, she comes up with her head
high from it, too.
And, like, she's a very strong
competitor.
The girl came to play.
>> PROBST: What would be your
concern about Jonathan coming
over?
>> Maybe he has a tendency to be
too much of a leader, and we
don't dig that over here.
We find out you're leading
around here, we'll cut you up,
you know?
>> PROBST: Jonathan, hearing
Nate say that, is it a fair
assessment?
>> You know, yes, I'm an odd man
out at this point, and I do want
to fit in.
You know, in the last 24 hours,
I think I've at least tried to
certainly not step on anybody's
toes and tried to, you know,
provide.
>> PROBST: Brad, did you sense
any tension in this tribe?
>> I like Jonathan.
I like Candice from the six
hours that I know of.
I've got no qualms with them.
The only thing is, they're
stepping in late in the ball
game, and that's what I can see
as a huge deterrent for them
being successful within this
tribe.
And that's it.
That's the bottom line.
>> PROBST: Do you trust these
people in this tribe now?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Wow.
You don't trust this big, happy
family?
>> Do I trust the entire tribe?
Absolutely not.
I'm sorry.
It's been 21 days, and trust is
a big word to me, Jeff, and no,
I don't trust everyone on this
tribe.
>> PROBST: Okay.
If somebody has the hidden
immunity idol, and it turns out
that you do need to play it, you
would present it to me after the
vote.
The person with the next highest
number of votes would go home.
It is time to vote.
Candice, you're up.
>> Obviously, this is nothing
personal, but I'm hoping I'm not
the only one to vote for you.
Good luck.
>> I think you're a good guy, a
good leader, and a good father,
but you're coming in way too
late in the game.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jonathan.
Brad.
That's two votes Brad, one vote
Jonathan.
Brad.
Three votes Brad, one vote
Jonathan.
Brad.
That's four votes Brad, one vote
Jonathan.
The ninth person voted out, and
the first member of our jury,
Brad.
Brad, that's five, that's
enough.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, you need to bring
me your torch.
>> See you, guys.
>> PROBST: Brad, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, I can tell by the looks on
your faces you're a little
surprised to see that the jury
started with tonight's vote.
This game is full of surprises.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: next time on
Survivor...
>> I trust you completely.
>> PROBST: ...Adam and Candice
finally reconnect.
>> You and I are going to the
end.
>> Candice I'm a bit leery about
because we don't want Adam to
falter.
>> PROBST: In a never-before-
seen twist...
This bottle contains significant
information.
...turns its game on its head.
>> My experience overall has
been the best-worst experience
of my entire life.
I didn't know I was going.
I didn't know what was brewing.
It's kind of a sigh of relief
for me.
At the same time, parting is
bittersweet.
Anything is possible in this
game.
And making jury just proves that
point.