>> JEFF PROBST: previously on
Survivor...
>> It's every man for himself.
>> PROBST: Brad's comments made
Raro suspicious.
>> I don't know what's going on
with Brad.
I lost my trust with him.
>> PROBST: While at Aitu...
>> As much as everybody is
saying, "Let's stay together
with the six," it's going to get
ugly.
>> Candice and Jonathan
conspired to turn against their
alliance at the first sign of a
merge.
>> I am determined to not be the
guy who made the move too late.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
I'm offering each of you the
opportunity to mutiny and join
the other tribe.
>> Oh, my god.
>> PROBST: If you want to move,
step off your mat and join the
other tribe.
Three, two...
Candice is mutinying.
One.
Jonathan mutinies at the last
second.
Candice and Jonathan betrayed
Aitu, leaving them with only
four members.
Go!
But in a dramatic twist, the
underdog Aitu tribe claimed
victory...
Aitu wins reward!
...and sent a message to Candice
by banishing her to Exile
Island.
>> Aitu.
>> Cheers.
>> PROBST: The reward brought
the Aitu four closer together.
>> The mutiny solidified our
commitment to each other.
We're a team to the end now.
>> PROBST: At Raro...
>> Took a step into the unknown,
guys.
>> PROBST: ...Jonathan tried to
fit in with his new tribe, but
quickly became the outsider.
>> To really think we all have
your back after we saw you sell
out your other tribe?
Are you dumb?
>> PROBST: Go, go, go!
At the immunity challenge, the
Aitu four sank Raro in another
upset win.
Aitu wins immunity!
On the other side of the coin...
Raro, tribal council tonight.
Before tribal council, Jonathan
tried to prove his worth by
working hard.
And Candice reconnected with
Adam and tried to distance
herself from Jonathan.
>> PROBST: But at tribal
council...
Brad, do you trust these people
in this tribe now?
>> Absolutely not.
>> PROBST: ...Brad dug his own
grave.
The ninth person voted out, and
the first member of our jury.
Brad, the tribe has spoken.
11 are left, and the jury has
its first member.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Who knew a Jew could climb a
tree and get coconuts and
pandamas nuts and scallops and
clams alone in the wilderness?
I'm the wandering Jew without a
tribe.
I'm living a mutineers' life,
man.
I'm on the outside.
I've made the game much harder
for myself.
>> Thanks.
>> You're welcome.
>> I regret jumping.
I mean, it was an impulsive
thing.
But I hope in the long run it
turns out to be a good thing.
>> So are you excited to be
back?
>> I'm so excited.
I mean... you know I trust you.
>> So we've got to keep that,
because you and I are going to
be the end.
That's what we're doing.
>> Good.
I took a big step to switch
tribes, and I'm, you know,
completely out of everything
that's going on.
>> But you and I are going to
the end.
>> All right.
From the very beginning, I feel
like Adam is a very
straightforward person.
So I do feel lucky to have
somebody in the game that I can
trust right now.
>> Everyone knows that you and I
are pretty close.
And Jenny is the only issue.
She's probably worried that I'm
going to be with you, which I
am, and we've got to, like, not
let her think that.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Probably want to make babies
and have a house with a white
picket fence.
They're like the all-American
couple.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> If we stick to our five--
Nate, Parvati, Rebecca, Adam and
myself-- we'll get far in this
game.
Candice, I'm a bit leery about,
because I know, in the original
Raro tribe, that Candice and
Adam had a little attraction.
So I'm a little worried about
that, because we don't want Adam
to falter, and make sure that he
stays secure with our group-of-
five alliance.
>> I trust you completely, but
everything else is like a
crapshoot.
>> Exactly.
>> That hurt?
>> Thank you.
>> Feel better?
>> And this one, yeah.
>> This one?
>> And I cut my finger.
>> Where?
>> Right here.
>> And I cut my lip right here.
>> Did you?
>> Yeah.
>> Feel better?
>> Yep.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> You know, we're deep inside
of a hole.
We're three people behind at
this point, and we're being
tested in a way that few
survivors have been able to come
out of.
It's an incredible opportunity.
To be the underdog is amazing,
and I'm happy, totally happy, to
be the underdog.
>> Tree mail!
How well do you guys know your
nautical flags?
No letter, just this.
>> Whoa.
>> So I don't know if we have to
memorize all of these.
>> Tree mail was basically a
code.
>> Red, white, and blue vertical
stripes.
>> Red, white, blue, that is
"T."
>> So we're fiercely cramming.
>> "S" is the squares with the
gray in the middle.
>> For us, we don't really have
any strategic options other than
to win.
We are the underdogs.
All we have to do is our best.
We have to work together.
We have to be a team.
If we're not, we're screwed.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Come on in, Raro.
Aitu getting your first look at
the new Raro tribe.
Brad voted out at the last
tribal council.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: One bit of news that
I need to share with Aitu.
When Brad became the ninth
person voted out, he also became
the first member of the jury.
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: Okay, guys ready to
get to today's reward challenge?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Two tribe members
armed with a compass and
coordinate will race out to a
large 16-point compass rose to
locate treasure chests buried
under the sand.
Each chest has the next
coordinate painted on the top.
When you find a chest, race back
to your mat.
The next two tribe members, with
that new coordinate, will race
out to get another chest.
Once you have all four chests
back on your mat, untie the
chest and remove seven wooden
nautical flags.
Remembering that the flags
represent letters of the
alphabet, you will match the
correct flags with the
corresponding letters on the
board to spell the word
"Victory."
First tribe to get it right wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The winning tribe
will be flown to a nearby island
and take part in an umu, which
is a local feast.
>> Yeah, baby.
>> PROBST: Pork, lots of fruit,
home brew, which is similar to
wine, made locally, thus the
name, home brew.
In addition the winning tribe
will choose one member from the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island.
Raro, you have three extra
members.
You're sitting three people out.
Who's going to sit this one out?
Rebecca, Nate, and Parvati.
Take your spots, wait for my go.
Both tribes have their compass.
Raro, your first coordinate is
north-northwest.
Aitu, your first coordinate is
east-northeast.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Yul and Sundra out first.
Jonathan checking north before
he heads out.
>> Right here, right?
>> PROBST: Aitu digging for
their first chest.
>> North by northeast.
>> It's north-northwest.
>> It's north by northeast.
>> North-northwest.
>> PROBST: Raro already having a
dispute.
Are they in the right spot?
>> North-northwest.
>> Just dig.
>> PROBST: Yul and Sundra found
their first chest!
>> Yes, yes, yes, yes.
>> Man, come on!
>> What is this digging like
that?
Help him.
Help him, Jenny!
>> Come on, guys!
>> PROBST: Aitu making good
progress.
They can see the chest.
They've just got to get it out
of the sand.
Jonathan and Jenny now have an
eye on their first chest.
>> Come on, guys, get that thing
up!
>> You guys got it.
>> PROBST: Yul and Sundra coming
back with their first chest.
>> Coordinate, coordinates.
>> North by northwest.
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Jenny
have their first chest.
>> East.
East.
East-southeast.
>> East-southeast.
>> That's it, that's it. that's
it.
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Becky have a
line on their second chest.
>> East south...
>> Southeast.
>> No, no.
>> East-southeast.
Right here.
>> This is southeast.
>> PROBST: Adam and Candice
confused, losing time for Raro.
Ozzy and Becky back with the
second chest for Aitu.
Aitu leads 2-1, big reward on
the line.
>> Damn, we stink.
>> Yul and Sundra out now,
digging up their third chest for
Aitu.
Adam and Candice have found the
second chest for Raro, finally.
>> Come this way.
>> PROBST: They've been at this
chest a long time.
Raro has lost all momentum.
Yul and Sundra have their third
chest out for Aitu.
Aitu leads three chests to one.
>> West-southwest.
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Becky now
looking for that fourth and
final chest for Aitu.
Adam and Candice have the chest
out.
>> Run, run, run.
>> Southwest, southwest,
southwest.
>> PROBST: Got to get back to
the mat.
No!
Got to get back to the mat.
Jonathan and Jenny back on the
course now, looking for their
third chest.
>> West-southwest.
Southwest.
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Becky have
found their fourth chest.
Big reward on the line.
Losers, somebody going to Exile
Island.
>> Come on, guys, keep digging.
>> The hole's coming.
>> They're on their last chest.
We've only got two.
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Jenny
now have an eye on their third
chest.
>> Dig around it, Jenny!
Dig around it!
Dig with both hands, both hands!
>> I don't want to bury it with
my other hand.
>> I don't understand.
>> PROBST: Jenny just pushed
more sand back in the hole.
>> Come on, guys.
>> Stand up.
Use your legs!
>> Use your legs to pull it up!
>> We're trying!
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Becky have
found their fourth and final
chest for Aitu.
>> Everyone take a box.
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Jenny
still working on their third
chest.
Aitu now working quickly to
untie all four chests and remove
the flags.
>> Who's having trouble?
>> I'm having trouble.
This one is really tight.
>> PROBST: Very little sand
coming out of that hole.
Aitu now pulling out the flags.
Those flags will spell one word.
>> Come on.
I'm going to go to exile.
>> PROBST: Jonathan and Jenny,
they've unearthed the third
chest for Raro.
>> South-southwest.
>> PROBST: Got to get back to
the mat.
>> Get on the mat, get on the
mat.
>> PROBST: Go!
Adam and Candice now looking for
that fourth chest.
Aitu has all the chests open.
They have all of their flag
pieces.
Adam and Candice like slow
motion over there.
>> Come on, both hands, guys!
Dig in!
>> PROBST: Aitu working together
quickly trying to solve the
puzzle.
>> Oh, my god, how do we keep
doing this?
>> PROBST: Aitu getting very
close.
>> I don't believe it.
>> "V-i-c-t-o-r-y."
>> PROBST: The new Aitu tribe
win said their third challenge
in a row.
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, my god.
Where are they?
They don't have the fourth box.
>> PROBST: Aitu, congratulations
on another victory.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: First order of
business-- you must now send one
person from Raro to exile
island.
>> One, two, three-- Candice.
>> PROBST: Is this from the same
betrayal?
>> Betrayal, strategy-- at this
point, same thing.
>> PROBST: Candice, you just got
back from exile.
You're heading right back there.
Boat will pick you up in time
for the next immunity challenge.
Aitu, we've chartered a plane
for you.
You will be flown to an island
where the feast is awaiting you.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff, head
on down the beach.
>> Yeah!
>> Thank you, Jeff!
>> Today, I did not want to be
sent back to Exile Island.
But I know it will be okay.
Sea cucumber-- so disgusting.
It's not fun to know that people
that you like want to see you
suffer.
I can survive out here.
It's tough, but hopefully this
is a character-building
experience.
>> I really believe that our
tribe deserved this adventure,
because we're up against these
amazing odds.
And we come into the challenges
humble, knowing that we can only
try our hardest, and that's all
we can do.
( speaking a foreign language )
>> At first, this very dignified
man in his costume, and all
these feathers, you know, comes
out and starts, like, yelling.
You know, almost like we had
done something wrong, you know,
like this very commanding voice.
Obviously we don't understand,
so, you know, the most we could
do was just stand and wait.
( chanting in a foreign
language )
( singing in a foreign
>> Basically, it was a warrior's
welcome.
That's part of their culture.
And we were warriors that just
came out of a fierce battle.
It was incredible.
And it was nothing that we ever
expected in our imagination.
( chanting in a foreign
language )
( cheers )
>> I didn't know I would ever be
a part of something this
beautiful in my life.
It was magnificent-- the people
welcoming us, how we felt after
winning the challenge, you know,
the four orphans that have to
stick together, and we triumphed
once again.
I can't even describe how that
felt.
>> Thank you.
>> So good.
Oh!
This is so good!
I was incredibly grateful for
the islanders reaching out and,
you know, being such wonderful
hosts.
>> Whoo!
Aitu!
>> It was fun.
You know, I got to say, probably
the first time since I've been
here where I really felt really
carefree and just enjoyed
myself.
>> Yul's a very complex, very,
very intellectual guy.
To see him come out of his shell
was amazing.
Man, that guy can dance.
I didn't know he had it in him.
You know, at this point in the
game, we've gone from being
separated into all of our same
ethnicities.
Now we're all able to come
together and experience a
totally new culture.
And we carry a piece of their
spirit with us into the next
challenge.
Raro doesn't know what's coming.
>> My tribemates all want to
chill.
Haven't yet seen that whatever
they're doing isn't working, and
maybe they're just demoralized
from losing.
But the reason we've been losing
is these have not been a tribe
yet.
They do not work together.
And I realized if it was ever
going to work, slowly but surely
give them an example of another
way to be in the tribe.
And that is you work your ass
off all the time.
>> Got some fish?
>> Dude, I got so many freaking
fish.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine,
ten, 11.
>> It looks like you went to the
store and just bought...
>> Yeah, right?
It's funny.
I'm getting the hang of it now
for sure.
These folks need to trust me.
I need to help them out.
I can continue to try to do what
I'm doing and have them say,
"Oh, well, at least somebody's
working.
Can't get rid of him because at
least I'm eating thanks to him."
I like it.
I don't know.
We'll see.
>> All right, ladies.
Tree mail.
>> Another map.
>> "Any explorer knows to study
about where he goes.
Disappointment shows, and for
the losers, the tribal council
lows."
>> Just learn the islands.
We got a whole map of the
islands of the Pacific,
assumingly to study.
>> Rebecca, you need to really
learn it.
Right?
Does that make sense?
>> There hasn't been one
challenge where I feel that
Rebecca has been a strong force
to help our tribe win.
>> I can help you.
>> Okay, help me.
>> Solomon drives solo, because
there's one little guy that
sticks out.
Solo.
So it goes...
Am I confusing you?
Should I go in order?
>> So I don't know how Rebecca
is going to fare from this point
on if she doesn't show a little
more in challenges.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Candice
returning from Exile Island.
>> Hey, guys!
Miss me?
>> Yeah!
Miss us?
>> Maybe just a little bit.
>> Welcome back.
>> PROBST: So Candice, since
the infamous mutiny, you've
spent three days and nights on
Exile and less than 24 hours
with your new tribe.
The isolation has to be having
some impact on you.
>> Well, I mean, I'd rather be
with my tribe, but I trust that
they know that I'm, you know,
staying strong out there, and
they're staying strong for me
back at camp.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Yul, I'll take back the immunity
idol.
Immunity is back up for grabs.
In tree mail, you once again
received information vital to
today's challenge.
I have faith that you studied
it.
On my "go," you will swim out
one at a time to a pontoon.
You'll dive down and unclip a
bundle of island names and swim
back to shore.
Then the next person goes.
Once all four tribe members are
back, you will move to an answer
table where you must correctly
identify ten islands by matching
the islands with the island
names you just collected.
First tribe to answer correctly,
you'll go back to camp with the
immunity idol.
Losers go to tribal council.
You will not, however, leave
empty-handed.
The losing tribe will take back
to camp with them this bottle.
Inside it is a note.
It must remain sealed.
The note contains significant
information.
You will bring it with you to
tribal council.
You will open the bottle after
you have voted.
Raro, you have three extra
members.
At the last challenge, Nate,
Parvati, and Rebecca sat out.
You three are participating.
Who is the fourth person who is
going to join you?
>> I am.
>> PROBST: All right, take your
spots at the start.
Wait for my, "go."
Here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Ozzy and Nate in the water
first.
When you reach the pontoon,
you've got to dive down and
unclip.
Ozzy already up with the island
names and heading back.
>> Man!
>> PROBST: Nate at his pontoon.
Nate didn't get it the first
time.
Raro quickly falling behind.
Nate has it, heading back for
Raro!
>> Yeah!
Come on, buddy!
>> PROBST: Ozzy back for Aitu
with the first bag of island
names.
Yul heads out for Aitu.
Raro's going to have to make up
some time.
Nate is exhausted swimming back.
>> Come on, Nate!
Kick it, buddy, kick it!
>> PROBST: Yul dives down for
Aitu.
>> Come on, Yul!
>> PROBST: Yul up quickly with
the second bundle of island
names for Aitu.
Nate coming back to shore.
>> Good job!
Good job!
>> PROBST: Jonathan heads out
for Raro.
Becky heads out for Aitu.
Aitu has two bundles of island
names.
Raro with one.
Jonathan up quickly with the
island names and swimming back.
>> Go, Becky!
>> PROBST: Becky slowing down.
>> Come on, Becky!
A little bit farther.
>> PROBST: Jonathan back to
shore with the second bundle of
island names for Raro.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Parvati heading out
now for Raro.
Parvati a strong swimmer, trying
to make up time now.
>> Swim, baby, swim!
>> PROBST: Becky is up with the
third bundle of island names for
Aitu.
Parvati has the third bundle for
Raro.
Raro is catching up.
>> Come on, Becky!
>> Push, Becky, push!
>> PROBST: Sundra heads out for
the fourth and final pontoon.
Parvati worn out.
>> Run!
That's it, that's it!
Nice job!
Nice job.
Go, Rebecca!
>> PROBST: Rebecca heading out.
Sundra can't get it on the first
time down.
>> Go, Rebecca!
>> PROBST: Rebecca has reached
the fourth pontoon for Raro.
Sundra has the fourth bundle of
island names for Aitu.
>> Come on, Sundra!
You've got it.
>> PROBST: Rebecca does not come
up with the bundle.
>> Come on, Rebecca!
>> Good job!
Come on, baby!
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Aitu, start solving
it.
>> PROBST: Rebecca has the
fourth bag for Raro.
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: Aitu already at work
solving the puzzle.
>> No, no.
Guam is up here.
>> No.
>> Stand up!
Stand up!
>> PROBST: Rebecca getting close
to the shore.
>> That's it, baby!
Run, now run!
>> PROBST: Aitu very close.
>> Okay.
Ready, and untie!
>> PROBST: Raro now working on
the puzzle.
Aitu thinks they have it.
Stop working, Raro.
Stop.
Aitu wins immunity!
>> Good job, guys.
Good job.
>> PROBST: Aitu, congratulations
on your fourth straight win.
Safe from tribal council once
again.
Raro, we have a date at tribal
council.
And you have a bottle.
The bottle is sealed.
You will take it back with you
to camp.
Bring it to tribal council.
You will open this bottle after
the vote.
Candice, grab your stuff.
Head on back to camp.
>> What's in that little bottle
that Jeff gave us?
>> I think individual challenges
but no merge, or something weird
like that.
Or, like, we have to live on the
same beach, but no merge.
Once we lost immunity, there was
a little twist that whoever had
to go to tribal tonight was
going to get this bottle with a
message in it, and we couldn't
open it until after the vote.
>> I'm interested to hear what's
in that bottle.
>> I bet it says we have to,
tomorrow morning, get up and go
to the other tribe's island for
breakfast and merge.
>> I have this feeling of, like,
dread, like I don't want to open
it, I don't want to know,
because it's going to be
something really bad.
But who knows?
>> There's nothing happening.
>> Based on overall performance,
productivity around camp, and
performance during challenges,
we're going to have to break up
our five-team alliance and send
Rebecca home today.
>> I think it's good that
Rebecca goes today.
>> Yeah, I think that's good,
too.
>> Then after that, I don't
know.
>> Do you think that will... she
can get that to happen?
>> Jenny becomes a threat, and
we really have to worry about
Jenny after this vote.
At that point, she's going to
really try to get Candice off.
She's worried that I wouldn't
vote Candice out, which is true.
So Jenny might be the next one
to go.
>> He's a cool guy.
But I wouldn't turn on any one
of our original members for him.
That's not fair.
We've gone through too much
together, you know.
Even though there are times
where I wonder about certain
individuals.
The tribe's consensus is to vote
for Rebecca.
She's our weakest link.
But I would say maybe Jonathan
right now, just because of the
fact that he's not family.
You know, we want to keep it
Rarotonga as much as we can.
It's kind of a... it's a weird
vote tonight.
>> We've got three good-looking
fish here.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Beautiful.
>> Yeah, baby.
I believe they're going to vote
Rebecca out.
I believe.
I hope.
And through a frickin' lot of
hard work on my part the last
couple of days, I think I have
earned at least the right to one
more night.
>> I'm really curious about that
note.
>> Is it after the vote?
Is it after the... after the
results are read?
>> After the vote.
>> But who knows?
We don't know.
Who knows what it's going
to say.
>> It's going to be something
bad.
If it was something good,
wouldn't they give it to the
winning tribe?
>> PROBST: we'll now bring in
our jury.
Brad, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Brad is here to observe.
You're not to direct anything to
him.
He's merely here to listen.
Okay, as a tribe, you guys have
won three challenges.
Jenny, what can you do to change
something within this tribe?
>> I wish I knew the answer.
I still can't pinpoint it.
I think it goes back to
analyzing our strengths and
weaknesses.
I don't know.
I mean, from now, I guess we
just have to wait and see.
>> PROBST: Rebecca, let's talk
about what's going on at camp.
What goes on?
Fishing?
>> We know we have to move
forward and we have to stay as
positive as we possibly can, so
everybody goes out clamming,
crabbing, octopusing...
>> And also I got some fish and
some trochus.
>> PROBST: How many fish?
>> Today and yesterday, I went
crazy with the spear and caught,
like, 20, 22 fish in last two
days.
>> PROBST: 22 fish in the last
two days?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Parvati, now that
Jonathan is here, in the last
two days, he's got 22 fish.
Is it starting to feel like,
"Okay, Jonathan's growing on
me."
>> He's blending in.
Yeah, definitely.
Jonathan is a big part of this
tribe right now.
He's been basically nourishing
us so that we could have the
energy to perform today, you
know, and it's cool to have him
around.
>> PROBST: Adam, it's important
that you keep people around who
can keep your tribe strong, and
people that you trust, which
could present a dilemma.
You had two people come over who
left their old tribe.
There could be questions of
trust there.
But it's fair to say at this
point that Candice and Jonathan
both are now very strong members
of this tribe, and are helping
keep you strong.
>> Jeff, I'm tired of losing,
and it's all about productivity
for me.
It's been other reasons before,
and tonight it's about
productivity.
I don't like losing.
I'm tired of it.
>> PROBST: Can't get much more
clear than that.
Okay, before we get to the vote,
did somebody bring the bottle?
So you've kept it sealed?
>> Difficult, but we kept it
sealed.
>> PROBST: We will hold on to
that bottle until after we have
voted.
Once the vote is over, you will
open the bottle and read the
note inside.
Okay, it is time to vote.
Candice, you're up.
>> You did you great today, but
this is based on overall
productivity.
>> Jonathan, I think you're a
great guy.
You just came into the game too
late.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Jonathan.
Rebecca.
One vote Jonathan, one vote
Two votes Rebecca, one vote
Jonathan.
Rebecca.
Three votes Rebecca, one vote
Jonathan.
Tenth person voted out, the
second member of our jury,
Rebecca.
That's four, that's enough.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, you need to bring
me your torch.
Rebecca, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Okay, now it's time to get to
the bottle.
Parvati, before you open it, was
there a consensus as to what the
note inside might say?
>> The consensus is it's a
merge.
Am I right, guys?
But we don't know.
We're hoping you're going to
roll out a whole buffet for us
with coffee.
>> Ice cream.
>> Champagne.
>> PROBST: Let's find out.
Parvati?
I want you to open the note and
read it out loud.
"You've just voted out one
member of your tribe.
You will now vote out another."
That's not fun.
>> PROBST: Definitely not a
merge.
>> Not a merge, and not very
cool.
>> PROBST: So Nate, not only are
you not merging tonight, you're
voting out another tribe member
right now.
>> This is wack Arnold, man.
And now I'm thinking, if we had
this win today, they would have
been down to two.
Could have, should have, would
have-- spilled milk.
>> PROBST: There is no sign of a
merge.
It could be tomorrow.
It could never come.
Now you're down to five.
They're at four.
So, Adam, criteria now?
>> You know, I think Rebecca
stood out as one that wasn't
productive.
And there's no one else that
does.
So this is going to be much
tougher.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Candice, you're up.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jonathan.
Jonathan.
Two votes Jonathan.
Jenny.
Two votes Jonathan, one vote
Two votes Jonathan, two votes
Jenny.
That's three votes Jenny, two
votes Jonathan.
One vote left.
The 11th person voted out of
Cook Islands and the third
member of our jury, Jenny.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, you need to bring
me your torch.
Jenny, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, tonight you lose two more
members.
You're now down to five.
Maybe this is the wake-up call
this tribe needs in order to get
it together.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: next time
on Survivor:
>> He's back.
>> PROBST: At Raro...
>> Where's the water?
Have we got water?
>> PROBST: Jonathan hits a
breaking point.
>> I'm not going to lose because
you kids keep the get your asses
out of bed.
>> PROBST: At Aitu...
Yul shares his secret.
>> If it works out, it will
change the course of the game.
And things heat up between Adam
and Candice.
>> To be honest, I am completely
pissed off about tonight's vote.
Jonathan did a great job of
pulling his own weight.
I respect that.
But in the end, I feel
completely burned because I was
blindsided.
And had I known or expected that
there would be two voted out
tonight, I would have done
everything possible to make sure
I would still be in this game.