>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Drop your buffs.
It is now time to integrate.
The four-tribe ethnic
division...
You are the new Aitu tribe.
You are the new Raro tribe.
...dissolved into a melting
pot.
Two new tribes, a whole new
game.
At the new Raro tribe...
>> There are so many men on
this tribe now.
Seems like we got all the, like,
really big, buff guys.
Your pants are falling off,
Nate.
I'm absolutely going to flirt
with him.
It's what I do best.
>> PROBST: At the new Aitu...
>> I trust Yul, I trust
Candice.
>> I totally agree.
>> PROBST: ...new plans were
laid.
>> Becky came right to me.
She said, " Yul and I would
like to get together with you
and Candice."
I said, "I believe that I have
Flicka."
Stay with me and Candice and
we'll take these other two and
the five of us will go to the
merge.
>> PROBST: And Yul solidified
his bond with Becky.
>> I found the idol.
>> It's so awesome.
>> It's a huge advantage to
have someone that you absolutely
trust.
>> Oh, I'm so excited!
>> Give it all you got, go!
>> PROBST: During the immunity
challenge...
Yul going try to fight them off
as long as he can.
...Aitu was outmatched by the
brawn of the new Raro tribe.
Raro wins immunity.
Raro sent Candice to Exile
Island, saving her from tribal
council and jeopardizing the
Aitu alliance.
>> PROBST: Suddenly Becky was on
the chopping block.
>> Jonathan...
>> I thought Flicka was me, so
we've got a serious problem
here.
>> We have to let Becky go.
She's a princess out here.
>> She's not, like, weak, she's
strong.
>> PROBST: Yul and Jonathan
scrambled to save Becky.
>> If five of us vote for
Cecilia and three of you vote
for Becky, then all of a sudden
you're on the outside.
Trying to convince Flicka and
Cao Boi to vote with us is the
key.
If not, then, all bets are off
and it's going to be a whole
different kettle of fish.
>> PROBST: At tribal council it
came down to Becky or Cecilia.
In the end, it was Ozzy's
former tribemate who was voted
out.
Cecilia, the tribe has spoken.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> At tribal council tonight it
came very close.
I received three votes and
Cecilia received five.
The alliance that I feel pretty
comfortable with and pretty
confident is Yul for sure,
Candice is right now on Exile
Island, she's still in the
alliance, and Jonathan said
that he would stay in the
alliance, too.
>> No, no.
>> Coconut.
>> I don't like hermit crabs.
I feel like I'm on the outside.
To lose the only member of my
former tribe, the person that
helped me lay the foundations
of everything that these people
are going to enjoy makes me
feel like crap.
If they want to vote me out
they should do it soon so I
don't have to keep catching
food for them.
I just don't feel like playing
along any more.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> Is that Candice?
>> Candice.
Look at her waving like Miss
America.
(laughter)
>> Candice!
>> Hey, guys.
>> How was it?
>> No idol.
>> Oh, man.
>> I think probably because I'm
the youngest, or whatever.
>> You think they did it, like,
as a bad thing?
>> I don't know, you guys are
asking good questions because I
haven't even thought about any
of this.
I didn't have time.
I think probably Adam and
Parvati told their tribe to
send me to exile.
But I don't want the rest of
the team to think that I have
some special, you know, get out
of jail free card from the
other team.
And everybody's like, "Yeah,
what do you think, what do you
think?"
And I said, "Well, I don't
know, I hadn't thought about
that."
You know, just played dumb.
>> Oh, I didn't even think
about that.
My mind is...
>> Feels soft already.
(laughter)
>> Like Sunday night football.
>> I know.
It was kind of annoying that
the guys were just sitting and
just waiting there and drinking
all the coconuts they could
drink and the girls were, you
know, working on improving our
shelter.
They're starting to rule the
roost a little bit.
I think they're getting very
comfortable with their position
in this tribe.
Because they know that we need
them, they're strong.
>> No.
>> No way.
>> You think they were?
>> I don't know.
>> Even if they all do think,
what's that going to do to us?
Nothing.
You know, we're all fired up on
how dominant and strong we are
as a tribe right now.
As a group of guys we're way,
way stronger than the other
tribe's group of guys.
And I think the testosterone's
flying a little bit and the
guys want to stick together.
These girls are going to need
manpower for sure.
So the four guy alliance is
definitely relaxed.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Raro, getting your first look
at the new Aitu tribe.
Cecilia voted out at the last
tribal council.
All right, today's challenge is
for reward.
Each tribe will select two
tribe members to be attached by
belt to a very long rope that
snakes over, under and around a
series of obstacles.
The rest of the tribe will push
and pull those two tribe
members through all of the
obstacles.
At the end of the rope is a
decoder table.
Once the entire tribe reaches
the table, one tribe member will
swim out to a barrel, dive
down, unclip a decoding wheel.
Bring it back to shore and the
entire tribe will use that
decoding wheel to decipher one
phrase.
First tribe to correctly
decipher the phrase wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Warmth and comfort.
Three blankets, two pillows,
one hammock.
In addition, the winning tribe
will choose one person from the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island.
They will stay there until the
next immunity challenge.
Raro, you have one extra member.
Who's sitting this challenge
out?
>> I am.
>> PROBST: Stephannie.
All right, we will get you
belted up and we'll get going.
Attached to the belt for Aitu
it is Becky and Candice.
For Raro, Jenny and
Cristina.
Here we go, for reward,
survivors ready.
Go.
Both tribes working the rope.
Teamwork critical in this.
>> Go Raro, looking good.
>> I got slack, I got slack.
>> PROBST: Easy to get confused
in this maze of rope.
>> Good job, good job.
>> Go under.
>> And under.
>> Go through the hole.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Aitu with a bit of a
lead.
>> Dig. Dig it.
>> Hole, hole.
>> PROBST: Raro moving on to the
log dig.
All the guys working hard to
dig out that sand.
Yul pulls Becky feet first
through.
She's stuck under the log.
>> Pull, pull, pull, doesn't
matter, pull.
>> PROBST: Got a face full of
sand.
Jenny goes head first for Raro.
>> Pull her out.
>> Pull her!
>> Her foot, her foot.
>> Don't worry about her.
Becky, you worry about your job.
>> We're doing great, now go.
>> PROBST: Aitu on to the next
obstacle.
Raro's through the log.
We are neck and neck.
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: Both tribes throwing
their members over these logs.
Blankets, pillows, hammock on
the line.
>> Let's not kill these girls.
>> We're fine.
We will give her a pillow
tonight.
>> PROBST: Aitu moving on to the
next obstacle, still with a bit
of a lead over Raro.
Raro now moving on to the next
obstacle.
Still a tight race.
>> Hold the rope, go up here,
go up here, Jenny.
Come up, come up, come up.
>> PROBST: Both tribes are neck
and neck.
>> Come on, baby, you're doing
great.
>> PROBST: Aitu's working
together well.
>> Keep going.
>> Hold on to me.
>> Come on!
>> We got to go under or over
the rope.
>> I understand that, but now
it's tangled.
>> Slack's not going to do
anything.
>> PROBST: Raro does not agree
on the strategy.
Costing them time.
>> Don't worry about that, good,
good.
>> PROBST: Aitu on to the
puzzle part of the challenge.
All eight got to touch.
>> Go, Ozzy, go.
>> PROBST: Raro's caught up in
their rope.
>> Come on, guys, it's not
over, stay in it.
>> PROBST: Ozzy getting ready
for a swim.
Raro's way back; Exile Island
looms.
Ozzy already has the wheel, he's
heading back.
>> Go, Ozzy.
>> PROBST: Raro not giving up.
>> Just get it in there.
>> PROBST: Now you have to
decipher the message.
Use that wheel.
>> Is that "A"?
"A," right here.
>> PROBST: Trying to figure out
which letter goes with which
number to solve the phrase.
>> Where's "K"?
>> It's not going to work.
What's seven?
11, give me 11.
>> "A", 11 is "A".
>> Six?
>> "L".
>> This doesn't work.
>> PROBST: Raro trying to
make up some time.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: They are still in
this challenge
>> Go, go.
>> PROBST: Brad into in the
water.
>> Seven is "W".
>> No, it's not working.
>> PROBST: Aitu nowhere close at
this point.
>> Come on, Raro, you're doing
it, baby, you're doing it.
>> PROBST: Brad has unclipped
the decoding wheel and heading
back.
>> Nice, Brad.
>> One is "W".
>> Are you sure?
>> PROBST: Both tribes working
on the puzzle now.
>> Try the small words
first.
>> Is 12 "T"?
>> This has got to be a vowel.
>> Five is "B", five is "B".
>> Cast away-- we're done.
>> We're done.
>> PROBST: Aitu thinks they
have it.
Aitu wins reward!
(cheers and applause)
Aitu, congratulations.
Pillows, blankets, hammock--
yours.
In addition, you have a
decision to make.
You're sending one person from
Raro to Exile Island.
They'll return in time for
the next immunity challenge.
They will not be exempt from
tribal council.
Who's it going to be?
>> Adam.
>> PROBST: Adam, you're heading
to Exile Island.
>> All right.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Let's go, Adam,
boat's waiting.
Aitu, grab your rewards.
Raro, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head on back
to camp.
>> Great job, guys, seriously.
>> We got the blankets.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> I definitely like winning
the last challenge because all
of us feel a little threatened
by the brawn on the other team
because they're so beefy, you
know?
>> This is amazing.
>> We came together when it
counted.
>> He's the fishing star for
sure.
Ozzy is a mad fisherman.
Caught eight fish or something
and he's out there for more.
Fantastic.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Nice job, man.
>> Look at this.
>> This a fish market here.
>> This is so great.
>> We're going to eat.
>> Wow!
>> I'm proud of you.
>> Today we caught 11 fish, and
I caught nine of them.
>> I keep telling him how proud
I am of him.
>> I'm happy being the sole
provider of this tribe.
I feel that I have the most
power.
If they lose me then they're
going to be losing a lot of
strength.
>> I think we should call him
Poseidon now or something.
>> Yes, King Neptune.
>> Because he's the god of the
sea, right?
(laughter)
>> Yeah, that was just so
frustrating.
>> Well, you guys, there's a
bright side to this.
We need to be humbled, (a).
We got humbled.
So, hey, no one is going home.
>> We were just bummed out that
we lost.
We took a lot of pride in
winning.
And then also bummed that Adam
got sent to Exile Island.
Well, let's cook because
nightfall's going to be here in
probably less than an hour.
>> Wait, they have to go on
rocks.
They can't go on wet.
>> J.P. is very demanding, and I
think he does it in a very sly
way where if you're not very
observant, you wouldn't even
realize that he's being
controlling.
But just the way he was sitting
in camp today like all sprawled
out with his back against the
like recliner on the throne and
everybody's just like waiting
on him.
>> Parvati, can you give me the
machete?
>> Where is it?
He's very demanding.
He's like, "Oh, hand me that
machete, hand me this bowl."
You know, "Serve me."
I'm like no, that just doesn't
fly with me at all.
>> Yesterday I was cutting a
coconut and they're like, "Nate,
come over here."
I was like, "What?"
Ow.
Oh, it's a crab.
(laughter)
I'm like damn, this nut hurts.
>> That's how I can get close
to guys in the beginning is
just flirting with them.
I mean, you just have to figure
out the best way to infiltrate
the little groups.
>> Really?
>> Yeah, guys are tight.
But, you know, we're tight.
You know that.
You don't believe me?
>> I believe you.
>> I know you believe me.
My feelings for Parvati are
that she's a very cool girl.
We click real good.
She's smart, but I can
definitely trust her.
She's definitely like... she's
my ace right now.
I think there definitely could
be some sparks in the future.
But I don't want to find myself
thinking like a dumb-dumb and
just... you know, just guys
sometimes, we can't control
ourselves.
They trust me.
>> By the guys, you mean J.P.?
He's the one who's calling
shots, he's the one who's
making the decisions.
>> Well, he is because he knows
he has me and he knows he has
the other guys.
>> I just don't like that he is,
like, completely in control
right now.
Or thinks he is.
>> But that's how you let the
game play-- let the king think
he's all good and sitting
pretty.
>> Is that your new motto?
>> I do not want to upset J.P.
right now.
That would be the last person I
would want on my bad side.
So I'm just going to let the
king sit pretty until something
happens.
>> Sitting in the nest, she's
probably got eggs.
>> Yeah, they got eggs.
>> Let's go look at them.
>> I don't know if she's
protecting eggs or she just is
tough.
>> I think she's got eggs.
The kid in me want to get some
eggs for everybody.
I don't need it but the kid in
me want to climb the tree.
The kid in me want to get up
there and see if I can do it.
Give me a stick.
>> No eggs.
>> Oh, my God.
>> What?
>> Oh.
Oh, wow!
>> The little chick.
>> Fell out?
>> Oh, man.
Just one?
>> Yeah.
>> Put it back in the nest.
>> Thing can't fly.
>> Oh, man.
Can't put the nest back, you
want to put the nest back?
>> No.
>> It wouldn't work, would it?
>> This thing is newborn, like
today.
Just covered with its... with
its stuff.
I mean, it couldn't hold its
head up.
It had been born within 24
hours.
And it's in my hand.
I mean, I wanted to cry.
I felt terrible.
I don't know.
>> We can't put the nest back
up.
>> We can try.
>> Okay, I'm going to put it
back for you.
Sorry.
I am really sorry, I mean it.
Curiosity got the best of me,
birdie.
>> The nest is really fragile.
>> Grab the tree branch.
>> We're sorry, mother.
>> Can you just put it on that
branch?
>> Yeah, that's where it was.
>> He's okay.
He's okay.
Forgive us, please.
>> Forgive us.
I'm sorry.
There, secure, okay.
>> Nice.
>> Good job.
>> I'm sorry.
That kid in me just keep wanting
to do this and do that, without
thinking.
And getting in trouble.
I should know better.
Why am I doing the stupid
things for?
I feel really bad.
I'm really humbled.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Adam,
returning from Exile Island.
(applause)
>> Welcome home.
>> Welcome home, brother.
Good to see you.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready for today's immunity
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Jenny, I'll take back the idol.
Once again, immunity back up
for grabs.
On my go, four tribe members
will race to assemble a stretch
of puzzle.
You will then run through the
jungle with the stretcher until
you reach the beach, where you
will find another tribe member
shackled at the top of a mast.
One tribe member will make the
long swim out, climb up a rope
ladder, release their tribe
member.
Both will then swim back to the
beach holding on to a life ring.
You will place the rescued
tribemate on the stretcher,
run back to the start where the
three remaining tribe members
must now build a rescue fire.
First tribe to build a fire big
enough to burn through their
rope, drop the tribe flag wins
immunity, guaranteed at least
one more day in this game.
Losers, tribal council,
somebody going home tonight.
Make sense?
Rarotonga, you have one extra
member, sitting somebody out.
Cannot sit out the same person
out in back-to-back challenges.
Stephannie sat out last time.
Who's it going to be today?
Cristina, take a spot on the
bench.
We'll get started.
In the mast for Aitutaki is
Candice; for Rarotonga it's
Parvati.
Building the stretcher for
Rarotonga-- Brad, Nate, Adam,
J.P.; for Aitutaki-- Jonathan,
Jessica, Ozzy and Yul.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
First step is putting the
stretcher together.
It is a puzzle.
>> Yeah this is a match, this
is a match.
>> PROBST: Raro with a bit of a
lead.
Aitu falling behind.
Stretcher coming together for
Raro.
>> Go, Raro.
>> Go guys.
>> PROBST: Raro first off with
their stretcher.
>> Go, Raro.
>> Go, hurry up.
>> PROBST: Aitu off with their
stretcher.
>> You got to get in the water.
>> PROBST: Raro with the lead,
Aitu right behind with their
stretcher.
>> Go!
Go!
>> PROBST: J.P. in the water
for Raro!
>> Get in the water.
>> PROBST: Ozzy with the long
run through the water.
J.P. swimming for Raro, Ozzy in
the water for Aitu.
We are neck and neck.
Ozzy just made up a lot of time
with a long run.
Who will be the stronger
swimmer?
>> Come on J.P.!
>> Let's go Ozzy.
>> PROBST:: Ozzy first to the
mast.
>> Come on J.P., let's go,
buddy.
>> PROBST: J.P. climbing up the
rope ladder.
Ozzy releases Candice.
They're both in the water and
on the life ring.
J.P. releases Parvati.
They're both in the water.
It's a race back to shore.
>> Come on, you guys.
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Candice with
the lead for Aitutaki.
J.P. and Parvati trying to make
up some time.
>> Come on you guys.
Come on Parvati, come on J.P.
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Candice in
the shallow water where they can
run.
J.P. and Parvati falling behind.
Losing time for Raro.
>> Lie down.
>> PROBST: Aitu heading back to
the start to build fire.
>> Come on you guys.
>> PROBST: Raro's catching up.
Once you hit the mat you can
start on the fire.
>> Go, go.
>> Let's go, guys.
>> PROBST: Raro back.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Stephannie, Jenny,
Becca start on their fire.
Both Aitu and Raro working on
the magnesium.
>> Get the flint going.
>> PROBST: Cao Boi flame for
Aitu.
>> I'm going to burn that.
>> Come on, baby, you're the
man.
>> PROBST: Aitu with a lot
of smoke.
Do they still have flame?
Cao Boi got his own system.
>> Yee-ha.
>> Don't lose it, stay cool.
>> PROBST: Cao Boi's either
going to be a hero or very
silly.
Raro not giving up.
You're still in this.
Somebody got whacked.
Jenny with a bloody hand.
>> Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Whatever Cao Boi was
doing, it's working.
Stephannie trying to get
something going for Raro.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Cao Boi with a big
flame now for Aitu.
Can they keep it going?
Raro needs to get fire quickly.
What you're doing isn't
working.
>> You guys want to switch off?
>> PROBST: Fire is going for
Aitu.
Raro has nothing.
Immunity on the line.
Tribal council for the losers.
>> It's up to the rope.
>> PROBST: That flame is burning
the rope.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> PROBST: Becca not giving up.
>> You guys are awesome.
Here it comes.
Watch the flag.
>> PROBST: Aitu wins immunity.
(cheers and applause)
Aitu, congratulations.
Once again you worked well
together and it paid off--
immunity.
(cheers)
Raro, not good news for you
guys.
Tribal council tonight.
Somebody from this tribe is
going home.
Head on out.
See you at tribal.
>> Well, unfortunately since we
lost our challenge today that
means we're going to tribal
council tonight.
And no one's looking forward
to that.
But it has to be.
Someone has to go home tonight.
>> Keep our heads up, guys.
I don't want to see any frowns.
>> Too bad we went up against a
Zen fire master.
>> I feel like I'm the weakest
link and I'm so angry with
myself about that.
Like I should have done better.
I should have struck the flint
harder, stronger, done
something, you know, to make
more of a difference.
>> Just so you know, when Cao
Boi was on our team he was
always the one making the fire,
starting the fire, tending to
the fire.
>> Look, guys, I'm the one that
caused us to lose this
challenge and I'm probably the
weakest link.
>> Steph just came out of the
blue and said, "I'm the
weakest link."
Stephannie and I are real tight.
We got Hikihood love, you
know?
She's one of my Supremes, so
she knows I have her back.
But then I think about it, all
these people are out here trying
to play a game and if someone is
doubting themselves this early,
and doesn't want to be here, I'm
not going to keep you here.
>> You know, rather than have it
be a surprise to her.
>> Give her some respect.
She's given us respect and
helped us out in many ways.
>> Exactly.
>> We give her the respect she
gave us, you know what I'm
saying?
>> You want to go fetch
coconuts?
>> I know it's important right
now as a tribe to keep the
strong ones in, that we can win
more challenges going forward,
but then again, it's five
women, four men.
So if we're going to do any type
of alliance, it needs to be done
right now, tonight, if any of
the women really want to stay
in the game.
I would love to see us girls
align and take out some of the
guys because the guys are
already starting to align
together and stick together and
they're the stronger ones.
>> So why don't we switch this
up and just have all the girls
align right now and get rid of
J.P.
>> That's what I said.
Women should stick together.
>> All right, I'm cool with
that.
I'm not ready to go home.
>> Girl, I'm not either.
>> Uh-uh.
>> Right. I can't believe I set
myself up like that.
I just should have kept it to
myself.
It was just a moment of
frustration.
I'm not giving up.
I don't want that perception
hanging over my head.
>> Hello.
>> All right.
>> How?
>> Us girls come together.
Are you up for it?
>> I'd be up for it.
>> Yeah.
>> Is she?
>> I really don't trust him,
I don't.
>> Honestly, I think...
>> We need you guys.
I need you.
>> I don't completely trust
Brad.
I trust him to a certain degree.
So whatever Brad chooses to do
today, I hope it's for the good
of our tribe and not just for
himself.
>> PROBST: Nate, how are you
feeling in general in this game
right now?
>> You know, we've only been
together three, four days.
So we're all still feeling the
waters.
I'm not breaking out of my
shell yet because it could bite
me in the butt.
If you become too powerful,
too assertive in the beginning,
the rest of them will just eat
you up.
>> PROBST: Jenny, is there a
leader on this tribe?
>> Not-- not really.
>> PROBST: And what does that
mean, "No, not really?" as if
there was something underneath
that.
>> You're putting me on the
spot, aren't you?
>> PROBST: It's tribal council,
it's a game for a million
dollars.
I'm trying to figure out what's
going on.
>> All right, J.P., don't hate
me, but J.P. likes to take
command a lot.
>> PROBST: So J.P., when Jenny
says "Sorry, don't be mad at
me..."
>> I have no problem with her
saying that whatsoever.
I mean, I don't say, "Hey, you
got to go fish, you got to..."
Matter of fact, there's times
I go, "I'm taking a nap."
You know, so, maybe I voice a
couple more things, maybe we
should do things.
But I don't tell anybody how or
when.
>> PROBST: Rebecca, why was it
you, Jenny and Steph that were
deemed the fire makers for this
challenge?
>> Because we were all really
confident going in, in terms of
making fire.
We've all started fires on a
daily basis.
And unfortunately, I just
couldn't get the right spark.
>> PROBST: Stephannie, would it
be fair to vote one of the
three of you off tonight simply
because you didn't get it done?
>> I would say no, it wouldn't
be fair.
It could have been any one of
us up there trying to make that
fire.
But that's not what you want
to consider.
If you're going to vote someone
off, you should consider the
big picture.
>> PROBST: J.P., while
Stephannie was talking, you
were nodding completely in
agreement.
>> Yeah, I mean, okay, I'll
put myself out there-- I got my
butt kicked on the swimming
today.
There was no reason for them to
vote me off today.
So I agree with Stephannie 100%,
it doesn't go according to the
challenge.
It's not fair.
>> PROBST: Brad, is it too early
to ask if there is a philosophy
that you bring to how you play
this game?
>> Trust is a foundation of
everything.
For me at this point in time, I
always like to use the term "go
with your gut," and 95% of the
time my gut's always right.
>> PROBST: Parvati, do you trust
everybody in this tribe at this
point?
>> For the most part, I do
trust everyone in this tribe.
>> PROBST: How about you,
Stephannie?
>> No, I don't trust everyone
in the tribe.
But I do feel comfortable
enough to share certain things
with all of our tribe members,
yes.
So there is a certain level of
trust that I have.
But to completely trust?
This is a game, and I can never
do that.
>> PROBST: Rebecca, when you go
back to camp tonight, will you
be able to let this vote go
easily?
>> It won't be easy but it's
something that has to be done
so that we can all move on and
move forward and get stronger
so that we don't have to come
back here again.
>> PROBST: J.P., you're shaking
your head.
You're dreading this?
>> Yeah, I've already told
myself this will probably be my
hardest vote in this game.
>> PROBST: Okay, now that Exile
Island has come into play, the
hidden immunity idol could come
up.
If it gets played, you present
it to me after the vote.
It is time to vote.
Stephannie, you're up.
>> Sorry, J.P.
It was either you or me.
>> I wish you didn't voice that
point of weakness, but you are
a wonderful and beautiful
person and you'll be with me
the rest of this game.
>> J.P., I know you had your
game face on and none of us
wanted to be played.
Good luck.
>> Your wish is my command.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Stephannie.
J.P.
Stephannie.
Two votes Stephannie, one vote
J.P.
We're tied-- two votes J.P.,
two votes Stephannie.
J.P.
That's three votes J.P.,
two votes Stephannie.
J.P.
That's four votes J.P.,
two votes Stephannie.
Fourth person voted out of
the Cook Islands...
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: ...J.P.
That's five, that's enough.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, you need to
bring me your torch.
>> Holy crap.
Damn, you guys outwitted me big
time.
>> PROBST: J.P., the tribe has
spoken.
>> PROBST: Well, you just voted
out someone who appeared to be
one of the strongest members of
this tribe.
He obviously did not see it
coming.
I'm hoping this means you have
a plan on how to get this tribe
better together to start
winning some challenges.
Grab your torches, go back to
camp, good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Today's a good day to be
just relaxing.
>> PROBST: Cao Boi fumes
over the women's work ethic.
>> Sundra, Candice, Becky
they don't even try.
They will be eliminated.
>> What you guys doing here?
>> PROBST: And Raro gets
unexpected company.
>> I don't think they should be
on our island.
This is our turf.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Wow, this is something I
never, ever saw coming.
It takes more than just being
strong and big and physical and
thinking you're mentally tough.
You got to really watch your
back.
There's no hard feelings,
that's the way the game is
played, and man, they really
pulled one over on me.
You definitely can't trust
anybody in this game, there's
no way.