( theme music playing )
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> JEFF PROBST: Tonight, on a
special edition of Survivor:
Cook Island...
>> We play for our team.
>> Right.
>> And when we're in the merge
together, we keep an eye out for
each other, and that's going to
be the difference between our
culture verses others.
>> PROBST: You'll see 14 scenes
of all-new footage.
>> Let's get this party started.
Keep it going, dog.
>> Throw it.
>> Stefannie had about three
swigs, and she's delirious.
>> Oh, yeah, hold her up.
( laughter )
>> I mean, we're getting blown
away from our island.
>> I know.
I don't know what to do about
it.
>> What is that?
>> I hope that's not them
flipped over.
>> Oh, my god.
>> PROBST: You'll see highlights
from the first 18 days of this
adventure.
>> Ah!
>> No!
>> Ah, stop!
I am so sorry.
>> I came here to play the game.
That's my dream.
My prize isn't even the million
dollars.
My prize was I fell in love in
this game, love at first sight.
>> Oh, my god.
>> What?
>> The little chick.
>> Oh, man.
>> This thing is newborn, like
today.
>> Wow.
I am really sorry.
I mean it.
>> PROBST: And we'll delve
deeper into Survivor's most
controversial season ever.
>> This was a racially based set
of tribes.
I think it'll be interesting to
see if there really is cultural
bias.
You know, the Asian tribe,
they're not all from one
country, per se, I'm assuming.
And I'm a white guy, but I'm a
white Jew.
>> You represent your race.
It's not about avoiding.
It's always a wall.
We can never let that wall down
to interact or be honest with
others.
>> It's a little bit
uncomfortable for me.
It's like you're trying to
change the world in 39 days, and
that just made the game that
much harder.
>> Watch it, watch it, watch it!
>> PROBST: 18 days ago, 20
Americans began the adventure of
a lifetime.
They had just two minutes to
gather everything they would
need for the next 39 days.
30 seconds!
>> The chicken!
>> Forget about the chicken!
Let's go!
>> Get overboard!
>> Paddle.
>> Where's the Hawaiian sling?
>> The teams were actually
devised by ethnicity.
You had a Latino team.
You had an Asian team.
You had a Caucasian team.
And then you had an African-
American team.
So I was like, "Oh, snap, you
know, I'm not the only token
brother for once."
>> Ah!
>> I personally feel like the
division is kind of strange.
Like, I've never been separated
because of my skin color before,
and I don't really like it.
>> Row, row!
>> The Asian invasion!
>> I'm pretty, you know, as
Americanized as you can get.
At the same time, I mean,
growing up, there were times
when people would make
presumptions about me or make
fun of me or insult me because
of my ethnicity.
I remember when I was a kid,
every time we put up Christmas
lights, young kids would come by
and smash our Christmas lights.
>> To me, being a Dominican
American is just a conversation
piece.
Because, like, being a
Dominican, what is that going to
do for me out here?
I think that means squat.
I think the content of your
character means everything.
Building stuff, there should be
the shelter, plus I know how to
make a toilet.
>> You want the machete?
>> Well, no.
First I'll just explain it to
you, and then we'll all be,
like, on the same page.
We'll all have the blueprint.
>> Do you want them with us?
>> They're going to do the
leaves and stuff.
They don't really need to hear
all this part.
>> PROBST: At Aitu, Billy
quickly found himself on the
outs...
>> It was kind of obvious to me
that he didn't really know
exactly what he was doing.
>> PROBST: ...forcing Ozzy to
step up.
>> Oh, my god.
>> I mean, he may not be very
big, but he's an athlete, and
he's somebody who'd be pretty
good at this game.
>> Really good job.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: On Puka...
>> You've got a touch of bad
wind.
>> PROBST: ...Cao Boi resorted
to some traditional healing.
>> There, you'll feel better
now.
>> It looks like it's burned.
Does it hurt?
>> I've never been accepted by
the Asian community.
I just don't fit the stereotype.
It's a very dangerous position
for me to be in.
>> You all know what this is,
right?
Represent, represent, represent!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: At Hiki, Sekou
quickly emerged as a natural
leader.
>> Okay, everybody, focus, okay?
Focus on what we're doing.
>> Is it smoking?
>> Yeah.
>> Come on, oh, yes!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: And then almost as
quickly...
>> I need a break.
>> PROBST: ...burned out.
>> Want to do it?
>> Yeah.
>> It's all for you.
>> Hey, y'all, look, a boat!
Look!
>> What?
>> Yeah, we upgraded!
>> PROBST: But as this never-
before-seen footage shows, it
wasn't just Sekou who lacked
outdoor skills at Hiki.
>> Be careful.
>> Look at all the water in our
boat.
>> You know, we thought we were
all canoe tight, like, "Yeah,
we're going to row this thing
out."
That was easier said than done.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, no!
>> I'm trying to hold it!
>> We're a bunch of city kids.
It's not that we are black,
white, Asian, Latino.
It's not that.
We're city kids.
We have one person who's from
the South.
>> Oh, no!
Oh, you okay?
>> Yeah.
>> It's harder than it looks.
>> You know paddling isn't our
specialty.
>> No, the whole boat
experience, rafts, boats,
anything on water that...
>> I don't know everything, but
I never got on a boat that did
that.
>> I have no clue.
>> So are you getting in the
front?
>> It really doesn't matter to
me.
I'll do it either way.
>> I'll be in the driver's seat.
>> We're about to go out,
Candice and I, catch us some
food.
Ready?
I'm dying for some protein, so
hopefully we can catch some fish
and get that.
Hopefully by the end of the day
we'll have all that for us.
>> PROBST: Day two at Raro found
Adam and Candice eager for an
adventure.
>> PROBST: But when the weather
turned, the adventure went
south.
>> I mean, we're getting pulled
away from our island.
>> I know.
I don't know what to do about
it.
Found a little sandbar here to
hang out at, because every time
we try to start paddling, the
current's so strong, it actually
brings us straight back.
Cold?
>> Yeah.
>> We'd been out there for
hours.
We were exhausted.
It was awful.
I mean, we were shivering.
My knees were shaking.
My jaw was shivering.
We were wet, and it's just the
frustration wearing on you.
It's the worst situation I've
been in in a long, long time.
I want to do something.
I don't want to sit...
>> Yeah, I don't think we can
paddle it.
I really don't.
>> You know, we're just going to
have to sacrifice the boat.
>> What is that?
>> I hope that's not them
flipped over.
>> Oh, my god.
>> I don't even see a boat.
>> You know, with the wind and
the current, I mean, we were
shivering, and we were freezing,
and we were exhausted.
It was awful.
But we finally made it back.
>> Can you see the little speck
out there?
>> That's our boat?
>> Yeah, I think so.
>> Did it flip over?
>> No.
>> Wait, it's not flipped over
or anything?
>> No, no.
It's anchored to the sandbar.
>> You couldn't paddle it?
You guys were too tired?
I was concerned about Candice
and Adam, when they came back
without the boat, and they're,
like, shivering and purple.
And then after I got over my
initial concern, I'm concerned
about the boat.
We need that to go fishing.
Like, we need food.
>> I just can't stand giving up,
you know?
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Save the other leaves for
when we make the tent for
tomorrow.
>> Why do you say we need more
cross bars?
>> Because when you look
underneath, they're starting to
bow.
We probably just need one more.
>> Oh, okay, that's fine.
>> All right.
>> There's a couple here.
>> PROBST: While the Aitu tribe
worked on their shelter, Billy,
in this new footage, went to
work on Aitu.
>> Well, strategically, first I
went up to J.P., and I set up an
alliance with him right away.
Me and him to the end, that was
the first thing I said.
And he didn't want to hear why.
He was just happy with it.
But we don't want to get caught,
like, a surprise challenge, then
we lose, and then right away we
go to tribal, and then we don't
know what we're doing.
The next thing I did was I went
up to Christa and Cecilia, and
I put the idea in her head.
It's like you want to hope for
the best, but you got to prepare
for the worst.
If you two are going to get
together, then I want to be with
you two.
>> Right.
>> You know, it's out there so
we don't get caught.
We can just like... you know,
whatever, give a sign.
>> Okay.
>> And then we know.
I was trying to play both sides
of the fence, because this game
shifts so much that if you rely
on just one alliance or one
person to get you to the end,
you're not going to make it.
>> PROBST: Hiki has their torch!
They're coming back!
At the first immunity challenge
on day three...
Puka wins the challenge!
...Puka, Aitu, and Raro won
immunity and flint to make fire.
Hiki was not so lucky.
No fire for you, somebody going
home.
But a surprise was revealed.
The losing tribe will choose one
person from any of the other
tribes to go to Exile Island.
And the two men of Hiki chose
Jonathan.
On Exile Island, Jonathan
searched for the hidden immunity
idol.
>> The idol!
I'm cold, miserable, shivering.
Exile Island's really terrible.
>> PROBST: Back at the Hiki
camp, as this new footage
reveals, the tribe considered
the consequences of losing the
first challenge.
>> I think today we learned a
lot about working as a team.
>> Rather than us trying to do
50 things?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't like being on a
losing team.
I don't like it.
But you know, we're sticking
together.
We're keeping our spirits up.
>> You know, it's only natural
that we're all just like...
I mean, I might not even say it,
but I think it.
>> Of course.
>> And it's just...
>> If you have any ounce of
awareness, you know, I think you
do.
>> I knew that I gave it my all
and that should be enough.
But now, because it's been
divided by race, it's not
enough.
And that's how the group pretty
much feels, because we do, on
some level, feel like we're
representing a race.
If whatever we... if we lose a
challenge or we don't succeed in
something, it has nothing to do
with the color of our skin.
>> No!
>> Nothing.
We're just all people trying to
succeed in a game.
Now it was just figuring out who
was the weak link within our
tribe, which, again, doesn't
have anything to do with the
color of a person's skin, just
personality, who clashes.
>> PROBST: At the first tribal
council...
First person voted out of
Survivor: Cook Islands...
...the women of Hiki decided
that Sekou was their weak link.
Sekou, the tribe has spoken.
>> I knew my head was on the
chopping block.
Nathan kept warning me all along
that the sisters would stick
together.
I don't know, maybe they felt I
was taking a leadership role and
they needed to get me out.
There were some things that I'm
not knowledgeable about, but I
was willing to come out here and
learn.
I take a lot of pride in that.
You know, that's what made it
such an adventure for me.
>> Let me just say straight out,
like, I trust you.
>> No, that's what... you were
from the very beginning, yeah.
>> PROBST: On day three, Yul and
Becky formed an alliance at
Puka.
>> Sticking together, obviously,
would help us in the game.
>> I want to stay together.
I agree.
Yul and I are both Asian, both
Korean, that we're automatically
going to form alliances because
of that.
In Korean, you call an older
brother an opa, and he seems
sort of like an older brother to
me, and I trust him a lot.
>> Oh, this is good eating.
These are some kind of nuts.
I don't know what they call
them.
>> PROBST: Later, Cao Boi and
Yul searched for food and common
ground.
>> You mentioned the other day
that people assume that you're
Japanese.
Why?
>> I look... I look Japanese.
I go to Vietnam, they all try to
speak Japanese to me.
But then I tell them, "No, why
don't you look at a history
book?
This is your ancestor's face."
"No!"
"All of you look Chinese to me."
They don't like that, but they
do.
>> A lot of people can't
differentiate among Asian
Americans.
I mean, "Asian American" is a
very broad term that encompasses
a broad range of communities,
and we're not all alike.
>> Each one of us is an
ambassador of our own race,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> We play for our team.
>> Right.
>> And when we're in the merge
together, we keep an eye out for
each other.
That's going to be the
difference between our culture
versus others.
>> All right.
>> I'll see you, brother.
Good job.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: At Aitu, Billy wasn't
pulling his weight.
>> We lose Billy, we come back
stronger than ever.
>> PROBST: So Ozzy suggested a
bold plan to throw the challenge
and oust Billy.
>> Billy is just dead weight, so
we might as well cut our losses
now and get on with the game.
>> PROBST: J.P. was on board,
but Christina was skeptical.
>> I'm thinking, "You know, this
doesn't seem right."
I don't know if I can trust
Oscar anymore.
>> PROBST: But at the
challenge...
Puka's on the course.
Raro's on the course.
Hiki's on the course.
...Ozzy's plan went into action.
Aitu completely unconcerned
about this challenge.
Puka, Raro, Hiki all safe from
tribal council.
Aitu came in dead last and chose
Yul from the Puka tribe to go to
Exile Island.
Yul, boat's waiting for you now.
Before the tribes parted, Billy
thought he and Candice made a
connection.
>> PROBST: At Aitu's tribal
council on night six, J.P.
confronted Billy about his work
ethic.
>> I came here to play the game.
That's my dream.
>> Part of the game is trying to
involve yourself.
That way, people find...
>> Well, excuse me, I'm still
talking here.
>> That way, people find you as
value...
>> I'm still talking here.
You'll get your turn.
>> That way, people find you as
valuable.
>> I'm still talking here.
You'll get your turn, Mr. Bully.
>> Because obviously you're not
valuable.
>> My prize isn't even the
million dollars.
My prize was I fell in love in
this game, love at first sight.
Her name is Candice, and in
between...
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Candice from Raro
tribe?
>> Yeah.
After the last challenge, we
sort of mouthed the words "I
love you" to one another.
So that was my prize.
My prize was her.
>> PROBST: In the end, Billy's
tribe mates cut him lose.
Billy, the tribe has spoken.
>> Wow.
I learned so much about myself.
First of all, I learned what my
priority was.
I learned that I'm not motivated
by money.
I never was.
This game definitely favors
those that are willing to stoop.
That part of the game, I kind of
wish I'd have did without and
just played, you know, to have a
good time.
I'm definitely not the conniving
type or whatever.
That's not for me.
That was definitely the wrong
way to go.
>> PROBST: On day six, Yul made
the most of his time on Exile
Island.
>> Oh, mama.
I found the immunity idol, which
is probably the single biggest
stroke of luck I could have had.
>> PROBST: and in this never-
before-seen footage, Yul
destroyed the note and covered
up all evidence of him finding
the hidden immunity idol.
>> I didn't want the box lying
around on the island, so I
constructed a little raft made
out of coconut husk, and I'm
going to set it adrift.
>> PROBST: With the idol gone,
everyone else searched in vain.
>> Okay.
"Use the mast and an island to
form a letter.
Block out the south, and you'll
be doing better."
Okay.
So many places it can be.
I'm just going to cover a big,
wide swath 20 feet long and
three feet down.
If I don't find it, well, it's
not from want of trying, you
know.
Boy, I could use a toothbrush
real bad.
>> I have a good chance of
finding it if I'm digging in the
right place, but I guess anybody
has a good chance of finding it
if they're digging in the right
place.
And it's got to be in between
here somewhere.
>> "If the southern isle
vanishes, a salvation you'll
find."
That makes me think that I
should head that way.
>> I don't know if the idol is
even still here.
Right now I'm just kind of
digging wherever.
>> PROBST: All right, drop your
buffs.
On day seven, the four
ethnically divided tribes merged
into two very diverse groups.
You are the new Aitu tribe.
You are the new Raro tribe.
Two new tribes, a whole new
game.
>> Yeah!
( cheering )
>> One, two, three, Raro!
>> You just moved up, girl.
( laughter )
>> At first it's going to be all
smiles and "A pleasure to meet
you, and we're glad you're
here."
But in the back of your mind,
it's a game, and you're in it to
win it for yourself-- and first
and foremost, cold, hard cash.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: At the new Aitu
tribe, Jonathan and Becky
understood this immediately, and
the game was on.
>> I trust Yul.
I trust Candice.
>> I totally agree.
Becky came right to me.
She said, "Yul and I would like
to get together with you and
Candice."
I said, "I believe that I have
Flicka."
Stay with me and Candice, and
we'll take these other two, and
the five of us will go to the
merge.
>> PROBST: And Yul solidified
his bond with Becky.
>> I found the idol.
>> Oh, I'm so excited!
I'm so proud of you.
That's so awesome.
>> PROBST: Back at Raro, Parvati
saw an opening of her own.
>> There are so many men on this
tribe now.
It seems like we got all the,
like, really big, buff guys.
Your pants are falling off,
Nate.
I'm absolutely going to flirt
with them.
It's what I do best.
>> I think Parvati feels really
safe because the guys love her.
She's, you know, a happy-go-
lucky, young, adorable girl, and
I don't think they want to see
her go at all.
She's entertainment for them.
You know, it's like watching a
movie to them, sitting around
and letting her be adorable.
>> Bombs away.
>> Okay, mama, you do that one
more time, I'm going to come up
there...
When I first saw Parvati, I was
like, "Damn!"
>> Boys will be boys, you know?
There's nothing else going on on
this island.
There's no music, no anything.
So what else are they going to
think about?
They're bored, you know?
>> She likes to put on her buff
as a miniskirt.
It's great scenery.
>> So I want to get in tight
with all the guys, work on them
and manipulate them and stuff
like that.
Like, I haven't even begun to
work my feminine ways.
It's all a game.
The dating game, the game of
survival, it's all the same.
>> Give it all you got, go!
>> PROBST: During the immunity
challenge...
Yul going to try to fight them
off as long as he can.
...Aitu was outmatched by the
brawn of the new Raro tribe.
Raro wins immunity!
Raro sent Candice to Exile
Island, saving her from tribal
council and jeopardizing the new
Aitu alliance.
>> PROBST: Suddenly, Becky was
on the chopping block.
>> Jonathan!
>> I thought Flicka was with me.
So we've got a serious problem
here.
>> We have to let Becky go.
She's a princess out here.
>> She's not, like, weak.
She's strong.
>> PROBST: Yul and Jonathan
scrambled to save Becky.
>> If five of us vote for
Cecilia and three of you vote
for Becky, then all of a sudden
you're on the outside, you know
what I mean?
>> That's so not the point,
though.
>> Well, what is the point?
>> She is the weaker link.
>> I'm trying to think ahead of
that.
>> I'm not thinking ahead.
I'm not...
>> But this is a game.
This is like a chess game.
>> Hmm.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Jonathan and Yul's efforts paid
off.
Cao Boi and Jessica flipped,
saving Becky and sacrificing
Cecilia, Ozzy's original tribe
mate.
Cecilia, the tribe has spoken.
>> I didn't sell out for a
chance to be on that island
another three days.
Given that I did try to play the
game with some sort of
integrity, really, my word meant
a lot, so those people missed
out.
>> PROBST: On night eight, the
mood at Raro was confident and
serene.
>> How about "Amazing grace"?
Everyone knows that, right?
>> ♪ Amazing grace
how sweet the sound
♪ That saved a wretch
like me
♪ I once was lost
but now I'm found
♪ Was blind
but now I see... ♪
>> Yeah!
>> Thank you.
( applause )
>> That was tight!
>> That was beautiful.
>> You're really good!
>> That was very good.
>> That was touching.
>> Thank you.
>> Ah, ah, ah!
>> PROBST: On day 11, the kid in
Cao Boi got the best of him.
>> Oh, my god!
>> What?
>> Aw.
>> Oh, wow.
>> A little chick.
>> It fell out?
>> Wow.
I am really sorry.
I mean it.
>> This thing is newborn, like
today.
I mean, what do you with this?
>> I cannot put the nest back
up.
>> We can try.
>> Okay, buddy, I'm going to put
it back for you, okay?
Curiosity got the best of me,
birdie.
I'm sorry.
That kid in me just keeps
wanting to do stupid things.
I feel really bad.
I'm really humbled.
>> Forgive us, please.
>> Forgive us.
I'm sorry.
I intrude in your house.
There, secure, okay?
>> Nice, good job.
>> I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, the men of
Raro were content to kick back.
>> It's like Sunday Night
Football or something or Sunday
morning football.
>> I know.
>> The guys are starting to,
like, rule the roost a little
bit.
It was kind of annoying.
Because they know that we need
them; they're strong.
>> No way.
>> You think they were?
>> Even if they all do think,
what's that going to do to us?
Nothing.
These girls, they're going to
need manpower, so the four-guy
alliance is definitely relaxed.
>> PROBST: What J.P. Didn't know
was that his cocky attitude was
becoming a real thorn in the
girls' side.
>> Parvati, can you hand me the
machete?
>> Where is it?
Oh, yeah.
J.P. is very demanding.
He's like, "Oh, hand he that
machete."
You know, "Serve me."
That just doesn't fly with me at
all.
>> PROBST: While the men of Raro
were taking it easy, Ozzy was
bringing in the big haul for
Aitu.
>> He's the fishing star, for
sure.
Ozzy's a mad fisherman.
>> This is so great!
>> I'm happy being the sole
provider of this tribe.
If they lose me, then they're
going to be losing a lot of
strength.
>> I think we should call him
Poseidon now or something.
>> Yes.
>> Poseidon!
>> King Neptune.
>> PROBST: And Ozzy raised his
Survivor stock even further...
Ozzy just made up a lot of time
with the long run!
>> Go, Ozzy!
>> Ozzy first to the mast!
...when he and Cao Boi brought
home the victory for Aitu.
>> Here it comes.
>> PROBST: Aitu wins immunity!
>> Good job, guys.
>> Great job.
>> PROBST: Back at Raro...
>> Keep our heads up, guys.
>> PROBST: ...Stephannie
expressed some self-doubt.
>> PROBST: ...opening a door for
her tribe to make an easy
decision.
>> Someone doesn't want to be
here, I'm not going to keep you
here.
>> PROBST: But Rebecca and Jenny
concocted a different plan.
>> Why don't we switch this up
and just have all the girls
align right now and get rid of
J.P.?
>> That's what I say.
Women should stick together.
It's five women, four men.
So if we're going to do any type
of alliance, it needs to be done
right now, tonight, if any of
the women really want to stay in
the game.
>> PROBST: But when Artie
expressed reluctance, the girls
approached Brad.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: And, as seen in this
new footage, they approached
Nate as well.
>> Hey, listen.
>> Whoa!
No!
>> Yeah.
>> No!
>> Uh-huh.
You guys are stupid!
That's not smart.
We need his strength.
>> We'll be fine.
We're still stronger than the
other team.
I thought it was Stephannie too,
but...
>> PROBST: But J.P. was kept
completely in the dark.
>> And I was just so pissed at
myself and wanting us to win so
badly and not feel like I had
given it 100%.
>> Yeah, I hear you.
But you know it kills everybody.
>> I just set myself up to go
home.
>> You're a beautiful, beautiful
person.
>> Thank you.
He actually came up very
confident that I'm leaving
tonight, and I played right
along with him and said, "You
know, thanks.
I've had a great time.
I'll miss you guys."
So I basically played my tail
off on that one.
You know, I hate that it has to
be like this, but, you know, you
do what you do, and you go out
on top, and you smile, hold your
head high.
>> You've been... your face just
makes me... kept me going.
Definitely, definitely.
And I will think about your face
every single day.
>> Oh!
Thank you, baby.
I appreciate it.
>> I think this will be the
hardest vote ever any of us will
ever have to do.
>> PROBST: J.P. never saw it
coming.
At tribal council, everyone but
Nate pitched in and gave him the
boot.
Fourth person voted out of the
Cook Islands...
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: J.P., you need to
bring me your torch.
>> Damn, you guys outwitted me
big time.
>> PROBST: J.P., the tribe has
spoken.
>> My biggest attribute is my
loyalty, and I think my biggest
attribute was my biggest
downfall, because I think I
trusted people too much, and
everyone that I trusted ended up
not working out for me.
>> PROBST: On day 12, Aitu let
the reward challenge slip from
their fingers.
Jessica drops out.
Raro wins reward!
( cheering )
And Raro took home wine and
fishing supplies.
>> That's what I'm talking
about!
>> PROBST: that night, as seen
in this new footage, Raro
celebrated.
>> Are we just going to drink
out of the bottle?
>> Yeah.
>> We're swigging out of the
bottle.
>> I'm down with that.
>> We won some wine, so we're
getting our fade on, which is
quite nice.
>> That's what I'm talking
about, dog.
>> You know, we can all get
loose, and I think everyone's
real personalities are going to
kind of come out when we get a
little booze in us-- especially
Stephannie.
She don't ever drink.
>> Is it good?
>> It tastes like a buttery
Chardonnay.
>> We're all happy.
>> No!
( laughter )
>> Let's get this party started!
Keep it going, dog!
>> She's a lightweight here.
>> She drunk?
>> Mama's drunk.
>> I'm taking care of my mama.
I'm taking care of my mama.
>> Mama needs to lay down.
She hasn't eaten anything.
>> Oh, my god!
She's wasted.
( laughter )
>> Stephannie's, like, on some
drugs right now.
She is torn back.
>> Give her another shot!
( laughter )
>> It's funny, though, because
you can tell she's like the good
old Southern mom who doesn't get
faded.
So, like, a couple of sips, so
she's kind of like... she's more
than drunk.
Home girl's on another level.
>> You all right?
>> Hold her up!
>> Stephannie had about,
probably, like, three swigs, and
she's delirious.
She's just talking nonsense and
kind of almost passing out.
It's really cute.
>> Walk this way.
>> Good girl!
>> Okay, we need to get...
>> What are we doing with it?
>> We need some coconut juice.
We need to open up some
coconuts.
We need coconut pieces and then
a little bit of saltwater.
>> PROBST: On day 13, Christina
was getting on Raro's nerves.
>> Then we got to that pot, take
it to the water.
>> We're all annoyed by
Christina.
She tells people, "Can you do
this?
Can do you that?"
Christina is coming across as,
like, our new J.P.
So she better watch herself.
>> Mine are worse, aren't they?
Are mine worse?
>> Yours aren't that bad.
>> PROBST: At Aitu, Ozzy had a
difficult time getting Candice,
Sundra, and Becky motivated.
>> Do any of you guys want to go
out in the boat to the reef, go
do some relaxing diving?
>> Yeah.
The fish are right out there.
>> The reason that I hesitate to
go is that I get really cold.
>> Yeah.
>> If it was sunny, I would be
out there all day.
I feel like once I get really
cold, I'm just, like, sitting
there, and I'm no good for doing
anything.
>> It's starting to get really
trying on my patience, and it's
getting harder and harder for me
to motivate to want to go out
and fish when I know that I get
one-eighth of the fish that I
catch, and the rest of it goes
to, you know, some people that
aren't as deserving.
>> Go for it, guys.
It'll be a little hot.
>> Everyone get a crab who wants
a crab?
>> I'll eat the bones when
you're done if you're not going
to eat them.
>> Eat the bones?
>> I'm annoyed that these
princesses sit around.
They eat the most.
They consume the most calories,
and they expend the least.
They don't appreciate a darn
thing.
They appreciate when they eat it
that it tastes great.
But watch out, there's a knife
poised at your back at all
times.
>> PROBST: Later, Ozzy, Cao Boi,
and Jessica set out to explore
the neighboring island.
>> I don't want to go back,
almost.
>> PROBST: And they made a
surprising discovery.
>> Why is their tribe here?
>> How you doing?
>> PROBST: And Raro was not
pleased.
>> How are you, my man?
>> Hi, Cao Boi.
>> Parvati.
>> You're Parv...
>> Par...
>> Par-va-ti.
>> I didn't like it at all.
I don't think they should be on
our island.
This is our turf.
This is our territory.
They got their own island.
>> PROBST: On day 14, Aitu won
the immunity challenge.
Aitu wins immunity!
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: And Raro was united
on who should go next.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> PROBST: But Stephannie's talk
of home...
>> I can easily see myself going
home and getting some mashed
potatoes and gravy.
>> PROBST: ...made the tribe
question their decision.
>> She's already mentally
checked out.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Christina realized she was on
shaky ground.
>> Just her personality.
You know, it can be a little
nerve-racking sometimes.
>> PROBST: Fifth person voted
out of the Cook Islands...
But it was Stephannie who was
sent back to the home she missed
so much.
Stephannie, the tribe has
spoken.
>> Actually, I'm extremely proud
that I made it for 14 days.
Sure, I would have loved to have
stayed in the game a lot longer.
You know, anybody would be.
I think what took me out of the
game was the emotional aspect of
missing my family, and that
really started messing with my
psyche.
>> PROBST: After tribal council,
Christina confronted her
accusers.
>> For the past few days, you
guys have been kind of rude, and
I've notice it, like when it
comes to passing things.
You snapped at me twice.
>> I said you were annoying.
It's just the way... I mean,
it's just the way it is.
>> I never thought that's what
they thought of me.
But I'm going to stick my head
up high still.
You know, I've gone through a
lot of stuff.
I've been shot and all that
stuff.
I mean, yeah, that's a tragedy
of my life.
I know I survived a lot of other
things in my life, and I'll
survive this.
>> PROBST: But the next day,
Christina couldn't let it go.
>> I'm not a robot.
Just because I'm a cop doesn't
mean I don't have emotions.
I have emotions just like you
and anyone else.
>> Right.
>> And you know what?
I was going to say something,
and I'm like, "You know, what?
If they have a problem, they'll
say something to me."
And I actually asked Adam in the
boat, "Is everything okay?
Why are you yelling?"
You didn't say anything about
being annoying.
>> I'm just like, settle down.
I mean, it just... it's nerve-
racking sometimes.
>> Well, then you should have
said something.
>> I said you were annoying.
>> No, you didn't say it.
>> I don't know how else to tell
you.
>> Honestly, you didn't say it.
I swear to God you didn't say
it, and I never swear to God.
>> Well, I swear I did.
>> Maybe you thought you did.
>> Christina, I said it to you.
>> Nope.
>> She said over and over again
that she wished we would tell
her the way she is and be open
and up front.
You know, if she needs to know
it, then I'll tell her.
>> PROBST: At the challenge...
Good news/bad news.
Good news is the winners will
feast.
Bad news is you'll be feasting
at tribal council, because win
or lose, both tribes are going
to tribal council tonight.
>> Ooh!
>> PROBST: Go!
>> Let go.
>> PROBST: Aitu endured a brutal
test of physical strength...
Jonathan and Yul taking on Nate.
...and handed Raro a beat down.
Aitu wins the challenge!
Here's how it's going to work
tonight.
Aitu will go to tribal council
first.
You will vote somebody out.
You will then enjoy your feast
while listening in on Raro's
tribal council.
Thinking Jonathan had the
immunity idol, Cao Boi dreamed
up a scheme to get the idol out
in the open.
>> Plan Voodoo would split our
votes between Jonathan and
Candice.
I think the plan is ingenious.
I know that neither Jonathan or
Candice has the immunity idol,
because I have it.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Cook Islands.
...Plan Voodoo never came to
fruition.
Cao Boi, the tribe has spoken.
And Cao Boi's wild ways finally
got him voted him out.
>> I was perfectly comfortable
in terms of survival.
It was the human element that I
overlooked.
The Puka tribe caught me by
surprise.
I thought their parents had
taught them honor.
I thought they would know what's
right and what's wrong about not
screwing somebody over or back-
stabbing anybody, but I guessed
it wrong.
>> PROBST: After Cao Boi's
departure, Aitu indulged in a
succulent reward...
>> People in our group plain out
said, "You're annoying."
>> PROBST: ...while listening in
on Raro's drama.
>> Unfortunately, she just found
out our true feelings.
>> PROBST: Then another
surprise.
Aitu, you will now kidnap one
member from the Raro tribe.
They will be a part of your
tribe through the next reward
challenge.
Aitu, who are you going to
kidnap?
>> Nate.
>> PROBST: Nate, I owe you some
food.
Nate had a hearty meal...
Seventh person voted out of the
Cook Islands...
...before Christina was sent
packing.
Christine, the tribe has spoken.
>> Being a police officer, you
know, you would think you come
into a game playing it a certain
way and use my experience.
But you know, at the same time,
you realize you're human.
You're a person.
You're going to have emotions.
You're going to go through
different things like anyone
else.
I would do it all over again,
and I'm glad I got the
opportunity to do it.
>> PROBST: Where 20 once stood,
only 13 remain.
How will Nate's time at the Aitu
tribe affect strategy?
>> I've got my eyes open very
much.
>> PROBST: What further
adventures will the survivors
face next?
What future twists will impact
the game.
The losing tribe will take back
to camp with them this bottle.
You have ten seconds to decide
whether or not you change your
fate in this game.
Join us as the adventure
continues.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> I'd rather be on the same
page and know what's going on.
>> PROBST: ...Nate causes stress
for Aitu.
>> I was a little bit uneasy
about the fact that they we're
having this conversation right
in front of Nate.
>> He looks like a monkey.
>> PROBST: Ozzy's stock
skyrockets.
>> Good job, Oz.
>> PROBST: And one exiled
survivor takes a beating.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Ah, ha-ha!
Don't come around these parts!
He got served!
Yeah!
Sorry, but it had to be done.
>> That was painful.
I'm sorry.
>> No, come on.
Yeah, you got served!