>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
Get overboard.
20 strangers were divided
into four tribes-- Puka, Aitu,
Raro and Hiki.
>> Watch it!
>> Different ethnic groups.
Is that kosher?
>> I'm a little bit worried that
it might play out to
caricatures and stereotypes.
>> The Hispanics all come from
Caribbean or South American
background.
We're used to being in this
tropical setting.
>> PROBST: But at Aitu, Billy
quickly found himself on the
outs...
>> He didn't really know what he
was doing.
>> PROBST: ...forcing Ozzy to
step up.
On Puka, Cao Boi resorted to
some traditional healing.
>> There, you'll feel better
now.
>> It looks like it burns.
>> I've never been accepted by
the Asian community.
I just don't fit the stereotype.
It's a very dangerous position
for me to be in.
>> PROBST: On Hiki...
>> One person get firewood,
one person get bamboo.
>> PROBST: ...Sekou stepped up
the lead, but the tribe became
frustrated.
>> He likes to take a lot of
breaks and we've got too much
to do.
>> PROBST: At Raro...
( screaming )
>> Ah, no!
>> PROBST: ...Jessica let the
the tribe's chickens escape.
>> I am so sorry.
>> I'm not happy with Flicka.
I can forgive her, but I don't
have to forgive her.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Puka wins the challenge!
...Puka, Aitu and Raro won
immunity and flint to make
fire.
Hiki was not so lucky.
No fire for you; somebody going
home.
But a surprise was revealed.
The losing tribe will choose
one person from any of the
other tribes to go to Exile
Island.
And the two men from Hiki chose
Jonathan.
On Exile Island, Jonathan
searched for the hidden
immunity idol.
>> A cold, miserable,
shivering... Exile Island is
really terrible.
>> PROBST: Before tribal
council, the women and men of
Hiki were divided.
>> They're in threes.
They're going to try to vote
one of us off.
>> They're stupid if they do
that.
>> They're stupid.
>> The ladies and I are
thinking Sekou might be the
right person to vote out.
>> Them two are like peas in a
pod.
>> PROBST: Sekou tried to
convince Stephannie to vote
with the men.
>> Sundra and Rebecca, they're
very close.
The guys are very close.
So, of course, I'm the swing
vote.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
the first person voted out of
Survivor: Cook Islands...
Stephannie stayed true to the
women and Sekou was the first
person voted out.
Sekou, the tribe has spoken.
The good news is you now have
fire.
19 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> We need fire so bad.
We're like on day four, no
water.
We're just kind of like...
we're beat, you know?
>> It's sparking.
That'd be something.
>> Is it the wind, you think?
>> We were all a little
disheartened.
We want to represent well,
but we're feeling a little
bit added pressure of being the
African-American tribe.
>> We tried, and we just
couldn't get it going.
I don't understand what we're
doing wrong.
We should have fire, but that's
not happening.
>> We're going to make this
fire.
It is absolute desperation time.
We've got to do it now.
>> All right, I'm going to try
it.
>> Guys, it's lit.
What do we do now?
( laughter )
>> We've got a fire.
We've got a fire.
Whoo!
The fire was started by
Rebecca.
Girls, I knew they were all
going to step up and really be,
like, some tough sisters, and
that's what they've done.
And I'm so happy.
Burn, baby, burn!
>> This has been a great day
for our team.
We're figuring it out and
working as one team.
And I couldn't ask for anything
more.
>> The Aitutaki tribe is
doing really, really, really
well.
This morning we went and got
fish together, and we captured
like eight, nine fish and got
seven or eight clams, big ones.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
Look at our bucket.
>> Latinos are good workers.
It's kind of in our blood,
it's in our heritage.
>> As me and my partners were
running towards the arcade, I
heard the shots being fired and
I felt something hit my arm.
I fractured my humerus and
shattered my radius.
This morning, I brought up the
fact that I'm a police officer
and that I was shot, almost
losing my arm.
And that was a life-changing
experience for me.
Initially they were going to
take my arm.
The doctors told my mom they
wanted to take my arm because
it was so bad and I lost so
much blood.
>> Christina is a super strong
woman.
I definitely respect all the
stuff that she's gone through
in her life.
She's definitely a role model
as far as I see it.
>> So I got my arm back and came
back to work full time.
>> That's huge.
That's huge.
>> That's why I wear the bullet.
>> There are the chickens over
there, they're walking past.
Look over the clothesline.
>> We've been trying to figure
out how to snag a chicken for a
few days.
We've seen them running around
wild all over the place, so we
decided to make a chicken trap.
>> Once the chicken goes up top,
we can pull the net and it will
kind of catch them like in a
little bag.
>> Oh, you want to do it that
way?
>> Tina had her chance to set it
up, and I'm making a concerted
effort not to shoot down all of
her ideas.
But a lot of the ideas she has
are coming from somebody who's
not done a lot of camping, who's
not been in the outdoors a lot,
so they don't make sense to me.
>> I think we should stretch it,
like, wide across here and then
we'll create, like, a little
tunnel.
>> Let's do it.
>> Ozzy feels like he knows
everything, and he probably
does, but every idea has to
be his idea.
So he is getting under my skin
a little bit.
>> I think we can do it.
Look, we have this line
right here.
Christina and I, we don't click
very well.
I think it's because, for one
thing, she's a cop, and also
just the fact that I'm ten
years younger than her and I
understand, because if I had a
14-year-old telling me what to
do, I'd probably get a little
pissed off myself.
>> I feel like I've shown what I
offer to the tribe, so I feel
comfortable with my standing
within the rest of the group.
>> There is so much food
to cook.
>> There's more.
>> Oh, is there really?
>> Yeah, look.
>> Awesome.
>> Tina?
>> Is she upset?
>> Is she?
>> We got two chickens, woo-hoo!
We've got two of them at one
time.
There's two, right?
>> There's two, yeah.
>> Yes.
>> Good job, Yul, good job.
>> Day four for the Puka
tribe started out on a really
high note because Yul actually
caught two of the chickens.
We're really excited because
I think everybody was pretty
hungry for something
substantial.
Yul's a smart guy.
He's very intelligent and a
good person to have on your
side.
>>( inaudible ) I trust you
because I feel like...
>> No, that's what... even from
the very beginning, yeah.
>> Becky, she's a lawyer, but
she does a lot of non-profit
work.
I respect that and I don't
think someone like that
is likely to be in this game
just to make a lot of money, so
I trust her.
>> I would love to see one of
us do it.
>> Especially if there were,
like, Korean...
>> That's why I want us to stay
together.
Yul and I are both Korean, so
obviously there's a bond
there, and we're automatically
going to form alliances because
of that.
In Korean, you call an older
brother an oppa, and Yul seems
sort of like an older brother to
me.
>> Sticking together,
obviously, would help us in
the game.
>> I want to stay
together.
I agree.
Cool.
>> Oh, I think it's him.
Papa bear is coming home.
( screaming )
>> Oh, God.
Exile Island was really
terrible, but I came back to my
tribe and they're all very
happy to see me and I'm happy
to see them.
>> All over the place.
I dug around for the idol; I
didn't find it, unfortunately.
Now I've come back and, like,
these guys haven't done
anything.
How is the shelter for the rain?
>> Well, the most uncomfortable
part is the floor.
>> We slept on the ground.
>> Why don't we start a fire
and let's make this floor.
You know what I mean?
Because it's going to be
night four and we don't have a
real shelter for ourselves.
I don't understand why they
don't have a better floor.
Basically, it's the same shack
they've been in for three or
four days.
I don't understand that.
>> I'm really excited about
pimping out our palace.
>> Yeah.
>> Jonathan and I decided
to pick up the speed a bit and
try to get something done to
make our camp better.
But Parvati, Adam and Candice,
they like to gossip and waste
time and not really do things.
And I was just like, "Somebody
do something."
Let's get some things done.
Hey Adam, this is quite a bit
of work.
>> I think it's the dumbest
thing to be doing this.
Why do you think you'll sleep
better when it's raised than on
the ground?
>> It was wet and it was cold.
>> Yeah, but what does raised
going to do to change that?
>> We won't be on the wet
ground.
>> Do you two want a raised
platform?
>> I thought it sounded
nice.
>> I know you do, but these
two.
We didn't decide things as a
group.
I want to know what y'all's
opinion is, you two, on the
floor?
You guys haven't said anything.
>> I think the flat bamboo
would be comfortable and it's
already started.
>> It's crazy, I think.
>> Well, what do you want to
do today?
>> I just don't want to waste
energy on something that... just
to look good.
I mean this is...
>> I don't know.
Let's see if we can get this
floor done.
Adam is hungry and he's crabby
and he doesn't understand that
other people have other needs.
And I don't need him being like
that.
>> I won't.
I won't.
>> Oh, my God.
Wow.
We got five of them.
>> Oh, wow!
>> Definitely, I've been trying
to conserve my energy because,
(a), I don't have a whole lot of
energy to burn, and (b), I think
it's stupid to just waste
your time doing something you
don't know anything about.
So, since they know more about
spearing fish and getting
coconuts and whatnot, I just let
them burn the energy and I'll
just go ahead and have some of
whatever they catch.
>> You want to start getting
that net together for the
chicken?
>> We need to clean it off
nice and flat.
You know, it's really difficult
if everyone's not pulling their
weight, you know?
It gets tiring having to
tell someone what to do all of
the time.
I go, "Billy, can you do this?"
"Billy, can you do that?"
"Billy, can you do this?"
You know, I hate saying that.
>> Well, I think we all just
work together instead of kind
of going off in our own little
ways.
>> I agree.
>> It will work out so much
better.
>> I don't know, I guess I kind
of feel a little bit on the
outside sometimes.
>> They shouldn't... you
know what, you should...
>> It's like, I don't relate
the same way as, like... even
though I'm Hispanic, I don't
feel Hispanic, you know?
It's like metal is my culture
instead of Hispanic being my
culture.
>> I think that's good, because
you have differences you bring
to the group.
>> Oh, thanks, thanks.
>> So, I mean, we want you
to be included, be a part of
this group.
>> So you don't feel excluded,
like, you know, jump in.
>> I was working directly in
the hot sun, and I quickly got
a headache, and Cao Boi came in
with his magical powers.
>> There's a deep, deep red.
Yours is just red.
Yours will probably go away
within a day.
Most of the people I know in
my life, sooner or later, if
they're friends with me long
enough, they experience a red
mark, and it always work for
them, too.
You're done.
>> ( laughs )
Thank you.
It helps, a lot.
It felt great.
I asked him not to give me the
same kind of slash he gave to
Brad.
But apparently I guess I have
something here now.
But at least my headache's
gone.
>> Oh, I make fun of them all
the time.
You've got to be able to laugh
at yourself, first of all.
>> Well, of course, but, I
don't know, I think if you
were a little bit sensitive
about it because of the
situation...
>> I have no hang-up, you know,
and I can just make fun of it
and just laugh.
Like what do you call a
Vietnamese with three dogs?
>> I think the bigger picture
is, like, we get it, but a lot
of people won't get it.
>> Exactly.
>> I don't worry about what
other people think.
They get to my case because you
make this racist joke about
Asian people, and I just want
them to understand that to
represent your race is not
about avoiding the jokes.
>> If you're making jokes based
on racial prejudice or
stereotypes, it's just going to
confirm them in people's minds
that don't know any better.
>> Well, a joke is a joke,
right?
>> No, it's not.
>> No?
>> Can I tell you guys one more
joke that is not really
offensive to anyone here at
all?
>> No.
>> One thing about Cao Boi is
it's good to have a sense of
humor, but if it's at the
expense of a particular ethnic
group, I don't think that's
cool.
( snoring )
>> Just keep it as an option.
I think it could help us in the
long run because we're not
going to have to be carrying
his weight anymore.
>> Cecilia, Christina, Ozzy
and I were sitting together,
and I had it in my mind.
Thank God Ozzy brought it up.
And he's, like, "We should
throw the challenge tomorrow and
get rid of Billy."
>> That's making us look bad.
I don't want to do that.
>> It's a strategy.
We lose Billy, we come back
stronger than ever.
>> Ozzy, he really wants to
throw the challenge to get
Billy taken off.
And I'm thinking, you know,
"This doesn't seem right."
That will put us in a better
position all around.
>> It is really sad that we're
already saying, "Let's put
one of our guys off."
I still think we should all work
as a team, so it's
disappointing.
And I don't know if I can trust
Oscar anymore.
>> Tree mail.
>> Sorry, who's going to read
it?
I read the last one.
>> "Reward and immunity, your
only tribal hopes.
You are bound by honor and by
belts and by ropes."
>> "Collaborative thinking, you
must all move as one.
Another leaves the island by
the setting sun."
>> Be like an obstacle course.
>> Be like chained... chaining
together.
>> I don't know, this is good,
though, ladies.
We wanted something we could
all work as a team, so let's
do it.
>> We're ready, right?
>> This is obviously for
immunity, so we need this.
We're four down; everyone else
has five, so we definitely
don't want to lose another
member.
We have to win.
>> We're talking about in
this next challenge trying to
lose it, just trying to get
Billy out of our team.
And I was really kind of worried
about the whole thing.
>> You better get your head in
this game if you want to stay in
it longer because he'll take
you out.
He should be here right now with
us right now.
Why not?
Why isn't he here right now?
Why isn't he reading this with
us?
Why aren't we discussing it?
Why?
I know what I'm doing.
>> Billy's just dead weight.
At this point, it's only the
second tribal council, so we
might as well cut our losses now
and get on with the game.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Getting your first look at the
new Hiki tribe.
Sekou voted out of the first
tribal council.
All right, first things first--
take back immunity.
Once again, immunity back up
for grabs.
I'm going to read you a short
story about Captain Cook's
three historic expeditions into
the Pacific.
When I'm finished reading the
story, you're going to move as a
group tied together.
You'll go under and over a
series of logs.
You'll go through a field of
poles where you must untie and
gather seven answer plaques.
You'll cross a two-line rope
bridge over a pit of water.
Once you reach the finish,
you will use the seven plaques
to answer five questions about
the story.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge is
for both reward and immunity.
Hopefully this reward will come
in handy.
Two tarps.
With 34 more days out here,
you're going to get a lot of
rain.
So, to be clear, the first tribe
to finish gets the tarps; first
three to finish get immunity;
last to finish, tribal council,
somebody going home.
And once again, the losing
tribe will decide which tribe
member from the other tribes
goes to Exile Island.
Clear?
>> Clear.
>> PROBST: Raro, Aitu, Puka, you
each have one extra member, who
are you going to sit out?
Give you a second to strategize.
>> I'll sit out, I'll sit out.
>> I should sit, I should sit,
I should sit.
I'm like the worst at memory.
>> I'm bad at memory, too.
Totally... I'm out.
>> All right.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: All right, who's
going to sit out?
>> Me.
>> PROBST: Jenny, and J.P.,
Adam, take a spot on your
benches.
Everybody else, meet me over at
the start and we'll get going.
Okay, I'll read the story:
"James Cook's first voyage took
him to the French Polynesian
Islands.
Tahiti was his destination.
During this trip, Cook also
mapped the entire coast of New
Zealand.
His second voyage, Cook found
and named New Caledonia.
On Cook's final voyage, he
became the first European to
locate the Hawaiian Islands,
which he called the Sandwich
Islands.
This trip would be his last.
Cook perished in Hawaii in
1779."
Now, after hearing this story,
if you are not confident that
you remember all the details,
each tribe has a written
version on the table in front
of you.
Keep in mind reading the book
could cost you valuable time.
For immunity and reward,
survivors ready?
Go!
Three tribes heading out without
reading the book, only Aitu
taking the time to look through
it and make sure they are right.
Huge strategy move.
Everybody getting up and over
the log.
Nobody panicking.
Raro first through, Puka
through, Hiki working their
way through.
Puka's on the course, Raro's
on the course, Hiki's on the
course.
Aitu really taking their time.
Will it pay off?
Puka with their first plaque,
Candice with the first plaque
for Raro, Hiki has their
first plaque.
Aitu, now they're out in this.
Jonathan has a second plaque
for Raro.
Brad and Cao Boi getting a
plaque at the same time for
Puka.
They've got three plaques
total.
Candice getting their third
plaque for Raro.
>> Keep going, guys.
>> PROBST: Hiki, you're still
in it, but you're falling
behind.
Aitu finally on the board with
their first plaque.
Cao Boi and Brad with five
plaques for Puka.
There are seven plaques total.
Raro with their fifth plaque.
>> Hold on, I'm almost
there, guys.
>> PROBST: Jonathan gets Raro's
sixth plaque.
Hiki with four plaques, Aitu
with two, Candice working on
the last plaque for Raro.
Puka right behind.
Brad's got to get the last one.
We're neck-and-neck.
Puka and Raro.
Puka has it.
Let's go, Raro.
Puka first on the rope bridge,
Raro right behind.
>> Left, right.
Left, right.
>> PROBST: Hiki, you're still
in it.
First three tribes to
finish win immunity.
Loser's going to tribal
council.
Puka doing a great job on the
bridge.
It's Puka and Raro fighting for
reward.
Hiki starting to make up some
ground.
Aitu not panicking, but they're
not moving quickly either.
>> Here we go.
>> It's okay.
>> The island Cook named on his
second voyage was New
Caledonia.
>> You ready?
>> The last island he visited
was Hawaii, right?
>> Cook located the Hawaiian
Islands and called them
Sandwich Islands.
>> That's right.
>> His final words were last
to be visited was Hawaii.
>> Tahiti.
>> PROBST: Got to get on your
mats.
Puka wins!
Raro has it right!
Hiki working together well.
They're still in this challenge.
Immunity on the line.
>> Tahiti, yeah.
>> PROBST: Aitu finally on the
rope bridge.
Aitu is having a holiday.
Hiki thinks they have it right.
Hiki has it right!
( screaming )
Puka, Raro, Hiki, all safe
from tribal council.
Okay, first order of business:
after reviewing the tapes, it
is clear the challenge ended in
a tie between Puka and
Rarotonga.
You'll each be getting two
tarps.
All right, Aitu, the only good
thing about losing this
challenge, you get to decide who
is going to Exile Island.
A big decision to make.
Who's it going to be?
>> We're going to send Yul, the
strongest member over there.
So we'll try to weaken them up
there.
>> Yul, boat's waiting for you
now.
Head down to the beach, boat
will pick you up.
>> One thing left to do: Hiki,
immunity, no tribal council.
( applause )
Puka, you, too, are safe.
Raro, no tribal council.
Aitu, you know what that
means-- tribal council, date
with me, somebody going home.
Grab your stuff, head on back
to camp.
>> We lost the challenge,
basically on purpose, and I'm
sorry to say that, but it's
something that we had to do.
Billy dug his own hole by just
not working.
And his lack of work showed a
lack of commitment to the tribe.
And you guys are lollygagging.
>> Losing that challenge, it
just really bothered me.
It was such an easy game.
It just makes me realize that
Ozzy is very conniving.
He's just all for himself.
And I really see him trying to
control everything.
>> No, you don't have... I
mean, yeah, you can do it
like that.
I just like to...
>> So right now, the situation
is pretty bleak.
I just hope to God I can find
some opening, some crack to go
through and somehow pull it
out.
>> Going to Exile Island really
sucked.
There's pretty much nothing on
it.
I feel like I have a pretty
strong connection with the
members of my tribe.
I miss them, hopefully they
miss me, and it will be an
opportunity just to uncover the
immunity idol.
"Use the mast and an island to
form a letter.
Block out the south island and
you're doing better."
From the clues, I basically
take it that I have to line up
one of two possible isles to
get an "A" shape using the
isle and the mast.
The last bit of the clue is
that I have to make southern
island disappear, so I assume
that I keep walking up and down
the line until I can no longer
see the southern isle, and so
I've marked the place where that
occurs.
Oh, mama.
Oh, wow.
Yes!
It's a compass.
"You have just discovered
something of great value.
This immunity idol will keep you
safe from being voted off
at tribal council once only.
The last time you can use any
hidden immunity idol is when
they are four survivors
remaining in the game.
I found the immunity idol,
which is probably the single
biggest stroke of luck I could
have had.
If there is a clear opportunity
where it can change the game,
I'll use it.
>> ( inaudible ) in the water.
>> Would you rinse it out
before you put any stuff in?
>> Yeah.
You don't feel bad?
>> It's all right.
He's not trustworthy.
I don't feel bad, I really
don't.
>> Once I figured it out, I
didn't want to be in this tribe
anymore.
I think those two guys played
me for a patsy.
That whole taking your sweet
time basically was a game.
And once I'm gone, you're on the
block.
>> Exactly.
>> I hope they don't throw
another game just to try to get
rid of you.
My only avenue right now, my
only shot, is with Christina.
So, I just threw out there
that if I go now, she is going
next.
And it flies with her, like,
she understands it.
I really don't.
>> No, Ozzy's playing the
hardest.
>> Yeah, he really is.
In my job, I see people all the
time, they're always in a lie.
And I had this feeling about
Oscar...
I think Oscar's more of a
threat right now, and he has
been really playing everybody.
Why have we voted someone from
our own team off?
Let's be strong.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> I hope you do.
Honestly, I hope you do.
( speaking Spanish )
>> No, girl.
We're on the same page.
Look him in the eye, for real.
>> Okay.
>> Christina came up to me and
she asked me if Oscar and I had
any kind of alliance or any
kind of an agreement.
And we don't.
But she asked that in Spanish.
>> I'm just kind of nervous.
Just wondering.
>> As a police officer, she has
to trust her partners because
her life depends on that.
So I can imagine how a little
bit of that is coming into play
here.
But I hope she can trust me
because I'm being honest with
her.
I'm good with you, for sure.
So it's whatever we decide to
do is whatever we decide to do.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> I do think Billy is going to
stir stuff up-- going behind my
back and trying to switch
people over, trying to
flip-flop so that, you know,
maybe it's me because he wants
me gone.
Christina is probably going to
be the most sympathetic.
But if they want to throw me
out, go ahead and do it because
I know they're going to suffer
really bad if they lose me.
>> My best hope is that
somehow, someway, Christina
found a way to get in
Cecilia's ears and plant the
seed just long enough for her to
swing a vote.
So all my chips are on
Christina.
My hand is a weak hand, but at
least I got one queen.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
approach the flame and get
fire.
This is part of the ritual of
tribal council because in this
game, fire represents your
life.
As long as you have fire,
you're still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so
you are.
Have a seat.
So, let's talk about the first
six days.
Billy, did a leader step up and
say, "Here's what we're going
to do?"
>> Well, initially, we just hit
the ground running, but little
by little, Ozzy emerged as the
big voice.
This was his element; he's very
much an outdoorsman.
>> PROBST: Christina, do you
agree with Billy that Ozzy is
the leader?
>> I don't feel that he's a
leader.
I feel that he tries to take
control of certain things
because he does have experience
in this area; he feels a
little more confident in that.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, do you think
you're the leader?
>> No, I don't think I'm the
leader.
There are certain things that I
have specific knowledge of
that if I don't voice my
opinion, then it's going to get
done wrong.
But I think that our strongest
thing is we can all get things
done as a team and it gives us
a lot of pride because we know
that if we work hard, we're
going to be stronger than
anybody else.
>> PROBST: Do you think this
tribe represented themselves
well in the last challenge?
>> No, the last challenge-- not
really.
>> PROBST: Billy, when I asked
the question, you're like,
"Oh, come on."
>> Actually, a lot of our loss
had to do with me.
J.P. and Ozzy decided I'm
hurting the tribe way too much
and so they were going to throw
the challenge.
>> PROBST: You believe they
threw the challenge?
>> I know they threw the
challenge.
>> PROBST: J.P., you threw a
challenge?
With only five tribe members,
you're already willing to lose
somebody?
>> At this point, yeah.
I don't believe in having
to carry weight of somebody
who I don't believe is trusting
and who doesn't carry the
workload.
>> PROBST: Billy, are you
surprised to hear that trust is
an issue?
>> I understand that a game
is being played, but I fell
into a classic trap, and now
I'm on the chopping block.
>> No, no, no, no, no.
I hate the way he's trying to
sound like he's a victim right
now.
>> I was a player.
I'm not saying I'm a victim.
>> And you know how to say the
greatest things to make
yourself look so damn good.
>> I'm clawing and scratching
or whatever-- yeah, I'm playing
the game.
That's my dream.
>> Part of the game is trying to
to involve yourself.
That way people find you
valuable...
>> I'm still talking here.
I'm still talking here.
You'll get your turn, Mr. Bully.
>> Obviously you're not
valuable.
>> You're Mr. Bully, you'll get
your turn.
>> Call me whatever you want.
>> I don't give a rat's ass.
So, like I was saying, I'm
playing the game.
That's what I came here to do.
My prize isn't even the million
dollars.
My prize was that I fell in
love in this game, love at
first sight.
Her name is Candice.
And in between...
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Candice from Raro
tribe?
>> Yeah.
After the last challenge, we
sort of mouthed the words "I
love you" to one another, and
so that was my prize.
My prize was her.
>> PROBST: I've never heard
anything that surprised me more
than what you just said.
And I want to be respectful
because I don't know what
happened.
But what would she base feeling
the same way you feel on?
>> I think it's just, you know,
love at first sight.
I think it's just a rapport
thing.
>> PROBST: So you're absolutely
sincere now?
>> I'm dead serious.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, have you
noticed anything between Candice
and Billy?
>> Man, I haven't noticed
anything.
But, I mean, I'm not looking
for it.
It's new to me as it is you.
>> PROBST: J.P., what's your
take on the Billy/Candice
romance?
>> Listen, I'm sorry, but from
the beginning, he was sketchy.
Just shady.
From the beginning.
And if I seemed insensitive to
the whole deal, whatever.
But then he brings up things
like this love at first sight
stuff, I mean, it's just... oh,
hell, I don't know, it's just
random.
>> PROBST: Christina, is it
unreal?
>> I think anything's possible
in life, but I feel very leery
for Billy.
>> PROBST: Christina, you seem
to have a soft spot for Billy.
>> I just don't want him to get
hurt.
I just hate when people get
taken advantage of, and I
just... I'm not into the
dishonesty and to the
back-stabbing.
I just really... I'm, you
know, taking care of him,
at least, looking out for his
best interests.
>> PROBST: Okay, there's been a
lot said here tonight, and I'm
very curious to see how it
plays out.
It is time to vote.
Ozzy, you're up.
>> If I can't trust you now, I
won't be able to trust you
later on in the game.
>> The only reason why I'm
voting for you is because you
are the best player in the
Aitutaki tribe.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Billy.
Ozzy.
One vote Billy, one vote Ozzy.
Billy.
Two votes Billy, one vote Ozzy.
The second person voted out of
Survivor: Cook Islands-- Billy.
That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Billy, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> PROBST: Well, two issues
emerged tonight: work ethic and
trust.
It sounds like you just dealt
with the issue of work ethic.
The question is: how will you
deal with the unresolved issue
of trust?
Grab your torches, go back to
camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
Mother Nature fights back...
>> Look at him sucking
me.
>> PROBST: ...Parvati works her
assets...
>> I'm absolutely going to
flirt.
Aww, baby monkey.
It is what I do best.
>> When you have children,
you're screwed.
>> PROBST: ...And Cao Boi turns
up the volume.
>> The guy does not shut up.
>> ( laughs )
>> I came into this wanting
to live the dream of playing
Survivor.
I got... I lived that dream
for six days and I think it's
kind of cool that the heavy
metal guy's getting eliminated
by some guy named Ozzy.
My biggest regret is I didn't
play the way I wish I would of.
I didn't represent myself
well in the beginning.
But I'm not going to regret
anything because I still got to
live the dream.
Too bad there wasn't a
heavy metal tribe. I think I
would
have fit in better over there.