>> JEFF PROBST: previously on
Survivor...
Knowing they were outnumbered,
the men of Raro got to work.
>> I think they're definitely
trying to prove themselves to
the women so that the women
don't try to overthrow all of
the guys.
I love it.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
>> Pull it in.
Pull it in.
>> PROBST: ...together, Nate and
Adam were unstoppable.
>> Raro wins reward.
>> PROBST: And Jonathan was sent
to Exile Island, where he came
to a realization.
>> I dug for hours and there was
no idol there.
At this point I have to assume
the idol has been found.
>> PROBST: Back at Raro...
>> We've got to get that pot.
>> Oh, you know what?
We need some more salt water.
>> PROBST: ...Christina was
testing her tribe's patience.
>> We're all annoyed by
Christina.
She tells people, "Can you do
this, can you do that?"
>> Somebody help.
>> She'd better watch herself.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
>> Rebecca's not up.
>> PROBST: ...Raro fell short.
>> Aitu wins immunity!
>> PROBST: After the challenge,
the tribe was united on who was
next to go.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: but Stephannie's talk
of home...
>> I can see myself going home
and getting some mashed potatoes
and gravy.
>> PROBST: ...made the tribe
wonder if her head was in the
game.
>> She's already mentally
checked out.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
>> You know, I thought Christina
knew she was kind of, like, that
way.
>> PROBST: ...Christina learned
she was on shaky ground.
>> It's just her personality.
You know, it can be a little
nerve-wracking sometimes.
>> PROBST: But in the end...
The fifth person voted out of
Cook Islands...
It was Stephannie who was sent
home.
Stephanie, the tribe has spoken.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> When we came back from
tribal, there was a lot of
tension, like I knew there would
be.
And I knew that Christina was
offended by what had happened
during tribal council.
It wasn't intended.
It didn't mean to come out.
But Adam responded.
And unfortunately she got her
feelings hurt.
>> You know what's funny, is for
the past few days you guys have
been kind of rude.
And I've noticed it.
Like, when it comes to passing
things, you snapped at me twice.
>> I said you were annoying
tonight.
>> No, you didn't say that.
>> And then I left it alone.
>> You never said that.
When did you say that?
>> Talking about passing things,
you're like, "Give me that, give
me that."
I mean, it just gets...
>> I always say please.
I always say please.
>> No, you don't.
No, you don't.
>> I have heard Adam snap at
Christina and calling her
annoying and I thought that was
kind of a little bit of a low
blow.
She's used to being in control.
She's not used to people telling
her what to do.
And it's really showing.
>> It's your personality.
>> Well, you could have said
something to me.
>> Your personality is...
>> We have to accept you the way
you are.
That's it.
>> No, but you could have said
something if it was bothering
you.
>> We can't change you,
Christina.
>> It's not like you're sitting
around not doing anything and we
want you to change that.
>> You said I annoyed you.
>> I mean, it's just the way it
is.
>> I just don't understand.
I never thought that's what they
thought of me.
But I'm going to stick my head
up high still.
And I have gone through a lot of
stuff.
I have been shot and all of that
I mean, yeah, those are
tragedies in my life.
I know survived a lot of other
things in my life.
I'm going to survive this.
>> Nice.
Look at that.
One, two, three, four, five more
of them.
Jonathan and I went fishing this
morning.
We went out to my same little
spot that I like.
I'm getting to know that area
very well.
And I have a few special holes
in the coral that I like to
visit.
So I can catch ten fish easily
within an hour or so.
>> Oh, baby!
You got him!
Yeah.
Look at the size of that.
>> Ozzy can hold his breath for
two and a half minutes or
something crazy like that.
The kid's like an otter or
something.
I mean, he's a great fisherman.
He's proven that time and again.
We need his strength for the
group to move forward.
But as an individual threat, he
is the biggest threat.
Certainly if the merge were to
happen today, I wouldn't want
him around, because Ozzy as an
individual is a very, very
strong player.
>> Oh, please be good to us,
tree mail.
Ahh!
Ah.
It's a mast.
It's a sail.
>> Tree mail.
>> All right, guys, gather
round.
"This head-to-head match needs a
well-balanced team.
To win your first feast, you
will kick and you will
scream.
To win your first feast you will
kick and you will scream."
It doesn't say anything about
immunity.
I wonder...
>> I believe we should bring
him.
I'm the priest.
I like to carry him.
I feel like I'm holy.
I should bring it.
>> I would prefer not to have
it.
>> I would bring the immunity
idol with us at all time, every
challenge.
We should bring him.
I believe Atangaroa is the ocean
god of fertility, and he came to
us an immunity idol.
He's our extra member.
>> You're saying, like, that's
your spirituality.
>> It means something to me.
It would mean nothing to you, I
would carry it.
>> Yeah, but it means something
else to me.
It means that when we bring the
immunity idol to a reward
challenge that we're sticking it
in their face.
>> I know that you don't, so I
respect that.
But since we're a team, let's at
least get everybody's opinion.
>> Have it your way.
It's less of a burden for me to
carry.
I don't need to argue.
Hell with it.
>> Cao Boi, you know, he is
rubbing some people the wrong
way.
He does have to get talked out
of a tree once in a while.
You know, and nobody really
spoke up except me.
Do you understand where I'm
coming from, Cao Boi, or where I
think most of us are coming
from?
>> That's fine.
We're good sportsmen, and we
play, and that's fair.
You know, that's the American
way.
>> Cao Boi, he's gone through a
lot of things in life.
He knows a lot.
At the same time he is very
hardheaded.
I mean, he's just an
unpredictable guy.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Aitu getting your
first look at the new Raro
tribe.
Stephannie voted out at the last
tribal council.
All right, are you ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge is
physical.
Here's how it works.
Each tribe will select three
people.
Each of those three will be
stationed at their own post.
On my go, two members of the
other tribe will race out and
attempt to physically remove you
from your post and drag you
through the sand to their finish
line.
Once they have accomplished
that, two other tribe members
will race out and attempt to do
it with the second person.
First tribe to get all three of
the opposing tribe members
across their finish line wins
the challenge.
Make sense?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Want to know what
you're playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: It's good news-bad
news.
Good news is the winners will
feast on thick lamb shanks,
bread, apple cider.
Bad news is you will be feasting
at tribal council, because, win
or lose, both tribes are going
to tribal council tonight.
Both tribes will vote somebody
out.
Here is how it will work.
The winning tribe will go to
tribal council first.
You will have your tribal
council and vote somebody out.
You will then move to the jury
section, and you will feast
while listening in on the losing
tribe's tribal council.
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> PROBST: So not only do you
get food, you get knowledge of
what is going on in the other
tribe.
Because today's challenge
requires equal numbers of men
and women, Aitu, you have one
extra member, you must sit out a
man.
>> It's purely physical.
Do you want to sit out?
>> You want to sit me out?
>> PROBST: Who's it going to be?
Who's sitting out?
>> Cao Boi.
>> PROBST: All right, Cao Boi,
take a seat.
I will give you guys a minute to
figure out who is going to be on
the post, we'll get started.
Here we go.
On the post for Aitu, Candice,
Ozzy and Sundra.
On the post for Raro, Chris
Christina, Nate, and Jenny.
Starting with the women.
Survivors ready.
Go.
You've got to pull them off of
their post and drag them across
your finish line.
>> Get her leg.
Get her leg.
>> PROBST: Becky and Jessica
double-teaming on Jenny, trying
to separate her legs, get her
off that post.
Candice is not budging for Aitu.
>> Damn, lady, let go.
>> PROBST: Jessica and Becky
have Jenny face down now.
Candice finally off the post.
Candice getting back on the post
again!
>> Becky, grab the other leg and
drag her.
>> Drag her!
Just drag her!
That's it.
>> PROBST: Rebecca yanking on
Candice.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Getting very physical
between Candice and Rebecca.
Becky and Jessica making up some
ground now.
They've got Jenny.
They're dragging her.
You've got to get a part of her
body to touch this line.
>> Come on, Jessica!
>> PROBST: Go!
Jonathan and Yul taking on Nate.
Raro still working on their
first person.
They've got to get Candice
across that line.
Jonathan and Yul trying to get
Nate off that post, but he is
not making it easy.
Candice now on top of Rebecca.
Parvati can't pull them both.
Nate doing a great job fighting
off two guys!
>> There you go, there you go.
>> PROBST: Nate making Jonathan
and Yul really work.
They're getting closer with
Candice.
Candice takes Parvati down!
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Nate's over the line.
Go, go!
Aitu heading out to for their
last opponent, Christina.
Parvati very close with Candice.
Got to get her to touch.
Go!
Candice is across, finally.
Aitu with the lead.
Raro's got to make up ground.
Adam and Brad going aggressive
after Ozzy.
They've got to get Ozzy across
that line and work on Sundra.
>> You're choking!
Get off my neck!
>> PROBST: No choking!
>> Stay away from my neck.
>> PROBST: Watch it, Christina.
Be easy.
Ozzy fighting them off as hard
as he can.
He's outweighed by a lot.
Christina trying to pull
Jessica's pants off.
>> Girls, pick her up.
Move her forward.
>> PROBST: Christina making it
very tough on Jessica and Becky,
giving Raro a chance.
Adam and Brad working Ozzy,
getting closer.
Raro getting back in this
challenge.
Got to get that foot to
touch the line.
Go, go!
Adam, Ozzy, and Brad, worn out.
It comes down to this.
Becky and Jessica trying to get
Christina across their line.
Parvati and Rebecca trying to
get Sundra off the post.
>> Don't look at them!
Come on!
>> Roll, roll, roll, roll!
>> PROBST: Christina, watch the
hair.
Sundra not budging off that
post.
>> Grab her legs, Becky!
Grab her legs.
>> PROBST: Becky pulling at her
shoes now, trying to get hold of
something.
Becky showing some life.
Parvati and Rebecca still
working on Sundra.
They've got her arms free but
not her legs.
Becky and Jessica very close.
Christina not giving up.
>> Jessica, push her, push her.
>> PROBST: Got to get that foot
on there.
Yes!
Aitu wins the challenge.
It's over!
Well, I said it was going to be
a physical challenge, and it
certainly was.
Good effort, I thought, by both
tribes.
Here's now it is going to work
tonight.
Aitu will go to tribal council
first.
You will vote somebody out.
You will then enjoy your feast
while listening in on Raro's
tribal council, where Raro will
vote somebody out.
In addition, there will be one
more surprise revealed tonight.
See you both at tribal council.
Get your stuff, head on out.
>> It was fun but it was crazy.
>> I was so proud of the tribe
today in challenge.
Oh, my god.
We just worked together so
beautifully, because it was a
physical challenge, and we came
together and we did it.
>> It came down to the girls.
You guys were way more physical
than them.
>> Yeah.
>> Christina, when she is
realized she was going to have
to budge and I was going to make
her, he is started pulling my
hair and, you know, ripping my
clothes off, you know, so I
thought that was a little
uncalled for.
>> A cop ain't used to getting
her ass kicked, you know.
>> We did it.
>> We won ourselves our big
feast.
It was a great day.
But it was very hard to come
back and know that somebody is
going to be going home, though.
>> I had this dream, I was
dealing with all of these
supernatural people with
supernatural power.
And there was a shaman lady,
like this old lady.
And she had all kinds of credit
card applications.
And she asked me if I have an
American Express or Visa, all of
this stuff.
I'm looking at it, and I said
"What do I need it for?"
She said, "Well, you need three
of that and three of that."
And I thought three and three--
that's how you can defeat the
immunity idol.
You can flush it out.
And I woke up and I go, whoa,
"Plan Voodoo."
>> Cao Boi believes John has the
hidden immunity idol.
So Plan Voodoo would split our
votes between Jonathan and
Candice, forcing a three-three
tie.
And if Jonathan has the hidden
immunity idol, it would force it
to be played.
And so that way you accomplish
two goals.
One, you get the hidden immunity
idol out of Jonathan's hands
and, two, you get one of those
two people to go home.
That's very interesting.
>> Think about it.
That's the only strategy I could
think of that works.
>> That's a very interesting
idea.
>> I think the plan is
ingenious.
I know that neither John nor
Candice have the hidden immunity
idol, because I have it.
But it's a great plan to break
down Jonathan's alliance with
the members of their original
white tribe.
>> John has been to Exile
Island.
Yul and Candice have been to
Exile Island.
But Jonathan has been there
twice.
He actually had five days and
four nights.
So he has the most time.
And if we merge, the Caucasians,
they become real strong.
If they have five members
intact, they can knock us all
out.
>> We lost the challenge today,
and that gets a double whack--
not only back to back, but
losing the feast.
It hurts.
I don't want to talk to anyone.
But I can't have that attitude.
And I said, "Okay, I'm going to
get us food.
We're going to eat good tonight
regardless."
Adam I got another one!
I'll pull its fat ass out.
He's a big boy.
Whoa!
>> We have to go to tribal
council tonight.
And I'm bummed because I could
be the next one out of my tribe,
especially after last night's
tribal council.
Basically they were saying that
I'm trying to take control of
situations, I'm overbearing.
But I will see what I can do.
>> I would definitely give you a
chance.
I'm up for giving anyone a
>> Okay.
Would you give me a chance
tonight?
>> I don't know who I'm
voting... I really haven't even
thought about it.
>> I will definitely keep
fighting and keep working hard.
And if you guys give me a chance
I promise I will not fail you
guys.
>> I think my effort in the
challenge today helped me out,
but I'm bummed because I can be
the next one out of my tribe.
I don't know.
We'll see what happens.
I will try to talk to some
people, and hopefully it will
change some things and hopefully
I won't get booted out tonight.
And I'm sorry that we just
butted heads.
And I know that... you know, if
I annoyed you I'm very sorry.
But I'm just asking if you just
give me one more chance...
>> That's fine with me.
I will talk to the guys.
>> Okay, thanks.
>> Christina is obviously the
outsider of the tribe right now.
She's kind of tried to get us to
go against each other, because
I'm sure she's going to feel
like she needs to scramble at
this point.
>> I was just like, "Okay," but
obviously...
>> No, don't worry about it.
I think we've got a game plan
and I think we're going to stick
to it.
>> Christina's the one that's
going to be voted off.
And I don't think that's
changed.
>> Oh, my god, you're amazing.
Oh, my god.
>> Will you?
>> Yeah.
>> And I promise I won't let you
down.
>> I got you.
>> Okay, thanks.
>> Of course.
>> Christina is close with me.
A lot of good characteristics
about her.
She is gave it her all today,
which is good.
And that was enough for me to
say, "Maybe, you know, you could
be valuable."
>> Adam snaps at her so bad, I
think she feels like...
>> He needs to get some class.
You do not talk to a woman like
that in disrespect.
I'm scared that Jenny may be
tight with them other Asians on
the other team.
If they merge, and there's three
of them, she could cut us up.
>> Want me to cut while you
pull?
>> Whatever, yeah.
You can cut while I pull.
>> Okay.
>> If we were going to keep
Christina, Jenny would have to
go.
She's a good tough cookie.
I love her.
So it's a toss-up.
Christina's strong, but her
mouth's strong.
Jenny's sweet, but I don't know
if I can trust her yet.
So it would be kind of... you
know?
>> Oh, that feels great.
Thank you.
>> That's my biggest concern.
>> Okay.
>> We did not lose the challenge
today.
We won.
It was just a twist of the game
that said we had to vote
somebody off.
And the consensus is that Cao
Boi should go because he is
pissing people off.
Something as simple as, "I want
to take the immunity idol.
Well, that's what I believe in."
You know, so he is a bit of a
wild card, and it's time to vote
him off.
>> You're a J.
>> Cao Boi has this theory that
the white alliance is going to
take over the game so we need to
get them out.
And maybe it's a good idea,
because I'm suspicious of
Jonathan.
Maybe it's the way he will say
something, maybe the way he will
look at somebody.
And when it smells a little
fishy, then you're like, "Okay,
I don't know."
>> I'm in a tight alliance with
Becky, Jonathan, Candice, and
Sundra.
Although now I'm not sure.
The girls, it's possible they
might want to vote off Jonathan.
For whatever reason he seems to
inspire some level of mistrust
among everyone.
They think he is playing the
game very, very hard.
And their suspicion of Jonathan
has started to rub off on me a
little bit myself.
I mean, you know, if everyone
kind of universally holds
Jonathan in some degree of
suspicion, then it kind of makes
me wonder-- maybe I should, too.
>> We're brothers.
We've got to remember that.
>> Yeah.
>> Ozzy, have you got it?
>> It's hard to say if Plan
Voodoo is a good idea or not.
There is a lot of chaos in camp,
and people don't know who
they're going to vote for for
sure.
So I'm just trying to play it
all by ear as far, you know, my
gut instincts are concerned.
>> I do feel bad that people
have to go.
I'd like to try to play the game
with as much integrity and
honesty as I can.
I'm finding it to be very, very
complicated, because I feel like
people do trust me.
But as a result of that, they
think I'm in separate alliances
with them, and obviously I can't
be in alliance with everyone.
So for me it's a question of how
far can you get in this game,
and who do I trust?
>> Relax, we'll be okay.
We have plan voodoo in effect.
I believe I can trust Becky and
Yul.
That's gut instinct.
They are solid, solid people.
I have the utmost faith in them.
>> How's your stomach?
>> You feel totally stressed
out.
Are you stressed out?
>> Tonight, if I get voted off,
I will be shocked.
I don't believe that's going to
happen.
I've got some pretty tight
partners.
If I'm wrong, then I've been
outplayed, and the conspiracy is
much bigger than I can picture.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Obviously, Cao Boi, you've
brought the immunity idol.
A first.
What's the reason?
>> We should bring it since we
have no more immunity, do we?
We're about to vote someone out.
>> PROBST: I haven't asked for
it back.
What do you want to do with it?
>> He will be another member.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, what is the
deal with the idol?
Because sometimes you bring it
to challenges when you don't
need it.
Tonight you bring it to tribal
council when you don't need it.
>> It's one of the things that,
for example, Cao Boi feels
connected to it, and that he
should bring it.
Other people don't care.
And some people feel totally
against it.
So it's just kind of, like,
symbolic for other issues within
the tribe.
>> PROBST: Yul, tell me about
Cao Boi.
>> Cao Boi is a mixture of
shaman, cheerleader, I mean,
fire tender.
He is very loyal in his way.
I can't say I fully understand
him.
You know, he has his own
perspective on things.
>> PROBST: Cao Boi, typically,
care you understood by people or
are you often misunderstood?
>> Typically in life I'm either
hated or I'm loved.
It's one or the other.
I am often misunderstood.
But eventually, if I have the
time, a lot of people will come
to understand that I mean well.
>> PROBST: Yul, are there clear-
cut leaders and followers on
this tribe?
>> There aren't any designated
leaders.
I think Jonathan and Cao Boi are
the most vocal in terms of
stating their opinions.
I think Jonathan is what I would
call sort of a natural leader.
I think he is very good about
articulating his positions and
thinking for the group.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, is that a
fair assessment?
>> I appreciate him saying that.
But it's not like what I say
goes.
It's not a role that I assume.
I mean, I certainly don't
patronize these people or talk
down to them in any way.
I don't think I do.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, what do you
base a vote on?
I know you don't want to get rid
of anybody, and the tribe is
jelling.
>> Man, that's something that
has been going through my head
all afternoon.
I'm still not quite sure if I've
come to a conclusion, and I'm
trying to work it out and search
my heart and see what it's going
to tell me so that we can all
continue on.
>> PROBST: Cao Boi, what do you
draw on for your vote?
You assess this tribe, you've
got to get rid of somebody.
>> We're looking down the road
to the big picture to see what's
going on.
It's sort of like a chess game.
And so the queen is pretty much
undefeated on the board, but we
want to see if we can expose the
queen, find a weakness in the
queen.
>> PROBST: Okay, I'm confused.
What does the queen represent in
this game?
>> The queen represents
immunity.
It represents individual
>> PROBST: So tonight's vote is
trying to expose the hidden
immunity idol?
>> Yes.
Basically this tribe will walk
away and we will see a clearer
picture of what we need to do to
continue playing in this game.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
If someone has the hidden
immunity idol and it turns out
you need to play it, you would
play it after the vote.
You would then be safe from the
vote, and the person with the
next highest number of votes
would go home.
It is time to vote.
Jonathan, you're up.
>> I think I have to take any
wild card out of the game that I
can.
Good luck to you.
>> ( whispering ) Sorry, bub.
I lost my trust in you.
>> ( whipsering ) I hope we
stick with this Voodoo Plan.
Where is the immunity idol?
Let's hope it comes out.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Cao Boi.
Candice.
One vote Candice, one vote Cao
Boi.
Jonathan.
One vote Jonathan, one vote
Candice, one vote Cao Boi.
Cao Boi.
Two votes Cao Boi.
That's three votes Cao Boi, one
vote Candice, one vote Jonathan.
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor: Cook Islands, Cao
Boi.
That's four.
That's enough.
Unless you have the hidden
immunity idol, you need to bring
me your torch.
Cao Boi, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> PROBST: Well, the hard part's
over.
Now for the fun-- some food and
a little eavesdropping.
There's a spot for your torches
just off the path.
You can have a seat over in the
jury section.
>> It was a wonderful
experience.
I had a great time.
I didn't make it as far as I
planned on going, but that's how
it goes.
I did learn I am most vulnerable
among the Asian community--
people who are like me but not
like me.
I was aware of them in the
beginning.
But eventually I learned to
trust them.
I should have known better.
>> PROBST: We will now bring in
the Raro tribe for their tribal
council.
Raro, before we get to your
tribal council, I owe Aitu some
food.
Bread, lamb shanks.
It's heavy and hot.
Because I want you to have a
civilized meal, some napkins.
>> PROBST: Raro, a lot to look
at over there.
Cao Boi just voted out, and food
that I know you would love to
race over and get a hold of.
Not really, Adam?
>> I don't really like lamb or
apple cider.
I really don't.
We've got plenty of food at our
camp, so that doesn't bother me
at all.
>> PROBST: Nate, you seem quiet
tonight.
>> Snap, that smells good over
there.
And I'm not even thinking about
it, because we had a good
octopus dinner.
So, you know, it's all good, but
yeah, this loss was wack today.
I tried to give it all I had but
I guess we didn't have enough as
a team.
>> PROBST: Adam, how frustrating
is it to lose and lose and lose?
You have lost as a tribe 2/3 of
the challenges now.
>> It's extremely frustrating,
Jeff.
But today, Candice just set the
tone.
And not only did she is get a
good lead for them, but she wore
out Parvati and Rebecca.
I mean, it's frustrating.
But it just ended up that way.
>> PROBST: Brad, one of the
things that Raro has always
prided itself on was its
physical strength.
Well, today you don't match up
as well to Aitu, maybe, as you
thought.
>> They may have a stronger team
pound for pound, maybe.
But I think it's not about one
particular challenge.
You should really look at the
bigger picture-- who is working
their ass off at camp and who is
trying to get along with
everyone, who's biting their
tongue when they want to say
something.
>> PROBST: Christina, is there a
little feeling of a sinking
ship, loss after loss?
>> I don't think so.
You know what?
Sometimes when you lose, you
lose, you lose.
But that doesn't mean you're
completely done.
I mean, we still have a chance.
You know, we've just got to keep
our heads up high, and it will
be our time to shine.
>> PROBST: Brad, Christina took
a little criticism at the last
tribal council.
Did you feel badly for her?
>> I did.
I did feel badly for Christina,
because I believe that everyone
deserves the benefit of the
doubt.
And sometimes things are better
left unsaid.
And unfortunately it had to come
up in tribal council last night
in front of everyone.
>> PROBST: Jenny, when you got
back to camp, what went down?
>> Well, she was angry.
You know, people in our group
plain out said, "You're
annoying."
You know, I can understand how
she felt.
I know that it was embarrassing.
It was a shock for her.
But the way the feelings were
with the tribe, I mean, how can
you say something and not offend
her?
>> PROBST: Christina, you didn't
take it well when you got back
to camp.
>> It bothered me because I
think they're my friends and I
let my guard down, I guess.
And you know, I don't want to,
like, beat a dead horse, but
it's definitely a blow.
And this morning we competed and
I felt I gave it my all still,
whether what happened last night
happened.
>> PROBST: Adam, did you feel
that from Christina?
Today's challenge, did she
feel like a unified part of this
tribe?
>> I think she did.
I think she worked really hard
during the challenge.
It's not as if she wasn't
contributing to the tribe or
anything like that.
It's more of... her personality,
it just clashes with ours.
She can't change that.
That's just of the way she is.
>> PROBST: Nate, this was once a
big, happy tribe.
It's now dwindling.
You're going to lose another
member tonight.
At a certain point people will
start going, "I've got to look
out for myself."
>> Oh, yeah, most def.
It's survival mode.
You know, you're always
thinking, like, "Well, worst
case scenario, you know, it
comes down to this and that."
You know, you're playing
scenarios.
But I think right now we're kind
of like... we want to be the
fourth quarter crew that comes
back, you know, from behind and
just, you know, smokes them out.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Before we vote, there's one more
twist to tonight's tribal
council.
Aitu, you will now kidnap one
member from the Raro tribe.
>> What do you mean "kidnap"?
>> PROBST: They will be immune
from tonight's tribal council.
They will come over to your
side, sit with you.
They will have a plate of food.
They will return to camp with
you and they will be a part of
your tribe through the next
reward challenge.
Quietly confer, then I'll ask
you for the name.
>> PROBST: Aitu, who are you
going to kidnap?
>> Nate.
>> PROBST: Nate, grab your
torch.
There's a spot for it down just
off the path.
Grab your bag.
>> Welcome, Nate.
>> Watch out for sauce.
>> PROBST: I owe you some food.
You won't have a lot of time to
eat it, so dig in.
There's your cider.
Okay.
Now we get to your vote.
If somebody has the hidden
immunity idol and it turns out
you need to play it, you will
present it to me after the vote.
Jenny, you're up.
>> ( whispering ) You're a nice
woman, but our tribe is stronger
without you.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Before we get to the vote, Aitu,
time for you to go.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Let's get to it.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jenny.
Christina.
One vote Christina, one vote
Jenny.
Two votes Jenny, one vote
Christina.
We're tied two votes Christina,
two votes Jenny.
Christina.
That's three votes Christina,
two votes Jenny.
Seventh person voted out of the
Cook Islands, Christina.
Unless you have the immunity
idol, you need to bring me your
torch.
Christina, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, you got rid of J.P.
because you didn't trust him.
You got rid of Steph because her
heart wasn't in it.
Tonight you got rid of Christina
because she just didn't fit in.
Three votes, three very
different reasons.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: next time
on Survivor:
>> I would rather be on the same
page and know what is going on.
>> Nate causes stress for Aitu.
>> I was a little bit uneasy
about the fact that we were
having this conversation right
in front of Nate.
>> PROBST: Ozzy's stock
skyrockets.
>> Good job, Oz.
>> PROBST: And one exiled
Survivor takes a beating.
>> I really enjoyed being
on Survivor.
It was a great experience.
I was just disappointed I got
voted off so soon.
Basically I almost feel like I
was taken advantage of.
But you know what?
I met some really good people,
and I met some really awful
people.
But I guess that's part of the
game.
But it was just an awesome
experience overall.