>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> PROBST: As the last member of
the four horsemen alliance, Alex
became a potential swing vote.
>> At this point, obviously,
they're not all in agreement.
>> PROBST: In an effort to
better position himself, Alex
attempted to gather information
about the tribe's alliance.
>> It's all about observation
for me.
I'm trying to make sure I'm just
not seen or heard, kind of like
a ninja right now.
>> PROBST: And Alex learned that
Earl, Yau-Man, Cassandra, and
Dreamz had a pact to go to the
final four.
At a messy reward challenge...
Boo with a huge piece.
...Boo tore his way to victory.
Boo wins the challenge.
>> Finally.
>> PROBST: ...and sent Earl to
Exile Island...
>> Clue number two.
>> PROBST: ...where he read a
clue to the whereabouts of
another hidden immunity idol.
>> "Near a lonely tower of
rock."
I'll figure it out.
>> PROBST: Go!
In a tense immunity challenge...
Alex scaling to the top!
...Alex hung on for dear life.
Can he pull it off?
But lost his grip at the last
moment.
Boo wins immunity!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Facing tribal
council...
>> PROBST: ...Alex tried to turn
Yau-Man's allies against him.
>> Yau-Man's going to eventually
have to leave, so why not
tonight?
>> PROBST: But Yau-Man felt
confident.
>> We all agree Alex needs to be
taken out, so I do not think I
will need to use my hidden
immunity idol.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
First vote, Yau-Man.
...though Yau-Man's name came
up...
12th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury.
...the tribe stayed true to its
alliance and voted Alex out of
the game.
Alex, the tribe has spoken.
Six are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I'm making a back path to the
water well.
Sneaky is fun.
I can't wait to try it out.
>> If he has it, then what
happens?
>> ...if we should have a
disagreement or something like
that.
>> The plan is actually to get
rid of Boo next.
Now that Alex is gone, Boo is
up.
You know, you want to get rid of
the stronger people and people
you're not sure if you can
trust.
So everybody agreed that Boo
would be the next person.
>> He's going to go into the
challenges really fighting to
win immunity.
>> Everybody be careful when
you're talking about everything,
even hand gestures.
You can see that.
>> At this point, I'm definitely
having fun.
There's a lot more sneaky
conservation, there's a lot more
combinations going in my head to
say, you know, "Who should be
the four I should have, and how
do I get that?"
Getting rid of Boo first would
make my life much, much better.
( theme song playing )
>> "This reward is big and will
put a smile on your face.
Doing good for others is a prize
you can't replace.
You'll have to move swiftly, and
you'd better be built tough.
Only by using some bold moves
will you be good enough."
>> Holy crap, y'all!
You know what that means?
It's a car.
>> I didn't even get my license
because I didn't have a car, and
I feel it'd be a waste of time
to just have a license sitting
in your pocket and no car.
I just want a car.
If we're playing for a car and
it has anything to do with
strength or agility or any of
that stuff, I'm guaranteeing you
I'll win the car today.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
And then there were six.
All right, before we get to
today's challenge, I'm going to
show you what you're playing
for.
( cheering and applause )
>> That's an F-350!
>> PROBST: 2008 Ford Super Duty.
It can haul three tons.
It can tow 12 tons.
Dreamz, think you could handle
this truck?
>> You wouldn't believe what I'd
do for a truck like that.
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's challenge, you're going
to be tied together into two
teams of three.
You must maneuver over a series
of seesaws.
One person falls off,
everybody's got to go back to
the start.
Then you must crawl up and
through the cargo net tower.
You must then dig up a hatchet
buried in a sand pit.
The first team to chop their
rope and release the box wins
the first part of the reward.
That threesome will take this
truck and the box, which is
filled with school supplies, and
pick up a trailer that's
carrying a mobile school office
on it.
You're going to take all these
school supplies and the mobile
school office to a local school,
all of this made possible by our
good friends at Ford.
It's a very exciting day for the
school.
They, in turn, want to treat you
to a nice picnic lunch.
It'll be a fun afternoon.
But before you leave, the
winning threesome will compete
against each other to win the
2008 Ford Super Duty.
One more thing: the winner of
this challenge decides who goes
to Exile Island.
We'll divide you up, and we'll
get started.
We've drawn for teams: Dreamz,
Cassandra, Earl on the green
team; Yau-Man, Stacy, Boo on the
orange team.
Here we go.
First team to finish moves on to
the final round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Everybody's belted together.
Got to maneuver over these
seesaws, cannot touch the
ground.
If you do, you have to go back
to the start.
Yau-Man, back to the start.
Orange back.
Dreamz, Cassandra, Earl doing
very well now with a bit of a
lead.
Yau-Man falls off.
Back to the start.
Yau-Man having a hard time.
Dreamz, Cassandra, and Earl
nearly through the first leg of
this.
You're through, you're through.
Move on!
Boo, Stacy, Yau-Man, falling
behind quickly.
Cassandra, Dreamz, and Earl
making quick work of the cargo
crawl.
Yau-Man, Stacy, Boo losing a lot
of time on this leg.
Boo, Stacy, Yau-Man, they're
across!
They're in it!
Boo, Stacy, Yau-Man, you're
still in this!
Let's go!
Dreamz is out of the cargo
crawl.
Cassandra is stuck.
Boo, Stacy, Yau-Man are catching
up!
Cassandra's through.
Boo is not giving up.
He's pulling Stacy out!
Boo, Stacy, Yau-Man made up a
lot of time.
Nice truck on the line.
>> PROBST: Boo sticking with his
spot.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Boo has the hatchet.
Got to get it unwrapped.
>> Go!
Hurry up!
>> Yeah, come on, come on!
>> PROBST: Boo, Yau-Man, Stacy,
moving on!
>> PROBST: All right, for this
next part of the challenge,
you're going to compete in an
ax-throwing competition.
You each have two intersecting
ropes.
Your goal is to cut both ropes.
First person to cut both their
ropes wins this challenge, wins
the 2008 Ford Super Duty.
That person is also in charge of
deciding who goes to Exile
Island.
Here we go.
Pick up your axes.
Ready, aim, fire!
Boo splits his first rope.
Yau-Man launches and just
misses.
Stacy falls short.
Stacy and Yau-Man, you got some
work to do.
Here we go, ready, aim, fire.
Yau-Man cuts his first rope.
Stacy low again.
Boo bounces off.
Boo and Yau-Man, both only have
one rope left to cut.
Ready, aim, fire.
Stacy throws first and misses.
Boo just misses.
>> Damn.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man launches.
Yau-Man breaks his second rope.
( cheering )
Yau-Man wins the 2008 Ford Super
Duty!
( applause )
>> PROBST: All right, Yau-Man,
congratulations.
>> Thank you.
So I want to see if I can make a
deal with the car.
>> PROBST: You're going to
negotiate with the car.
>> I'm going to negotiate a
deal.
>> PROBST: Okay.
>> First of all, Dreamz, how
badly do you need that car?
>> You know how bad I need a
car, Yau-Man.
I'm the only one out here
without a car.
I'm talking out of everybody
here.
>> Okay.
Here's the deal.
There are six of us left now,
right?
>> Yes.
>> When there are four of us
left, if you and I happen to be
one of the four, if that
happens, if you win the immunity
for that round, you will give it
to me.
>> I'll promise to God.
>> When there are four of us
left.
>> When there's four of us left,
if I win immunity.
>> PROBST: So I want to be
clear.
You're saying, "I'll give you
the truck, and the condition is
that if we're both in the final
four together, and you win that
immunity challenge"-- Dreamz
does, he'll give it to you.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: Knowing you can't
enforce it.
It's his word.
>> It's his word.
>> I give you my word.
>> His word is good.
>> PROBST: Regardless what
happens, you get voted out at
the next tribal council...
>> He still has the truck.
>> PROBST: You're willing to
take that risk?
>> Yes.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: All right, Dreamz,
hop up on the platform.
That truck is yours, my man.
( applause )
>> You need a truck a lot more
than I do.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Enjoy it.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, you have one
decision left to make.
From the three of you left, who
are you sending to Exile Island?
>> Myself.
>> PROBST: You're sending
yourself?
>> Yau-Man is an amazing dude.
I don't get it, and I'm not
going to try.
Yau-Man is an amazing guy.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, you're the
first person ever in the history
of Survivor to go from winning a
truck to not having a truck and
going to Exile Island.
The boat's waiting for you.
>> Enjoy.
Have a good picnic lunch.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, you will
return in time for the next
immunity challenge.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: All right, Cassandra,
Earl, nothing for you.
Head on back to camp.
Dreamz, here's how it's going to
work.
We're going to load your truck
on to our barge.
We're going to float you up
river until we can get access to
a road.
You're going to drive to the
school.
I'll be waiting for you there.
In the meantime, check out your
new ride.
>> Whoo!
>> Well, today is the reward
challenge.
As the winner, I get to pick
someone to go to Exile Island.
Earl has been to Exile Island
once too many times, and I don't
think Cassandra would survive at
all.
So I end up electing myself to
go to Exile Island.
I think that's the first time
that has happened.
I feel very good about giving
Dreamz that car.
Certainly, that is the biggest
gift I have given so far in my
entire life.
He has the opportunity to
really, really change his life,
and I am very glad I'm able to
do that, even though it's based
on a strategic move.
My worry has been always when I
get to the final four, Dreamz
will probably be there, and I
need a way to get rid of Dreamz.
So I made Dreamz the offer that
if and when we get to the final
four together, that if he wins
immunity, he has to give it to
me.
I was very surprised he said yes
without much hesitation.
By giving away the truck is the
best way to get rid of my
biggest competitor, and I have
pretty much guaranteed myself a
free pass at the final four.
All right!
Electing myself to come to Exile
Island also gives me the
opportunity to get the third
clue, which would help me find
the rehidden immunity idol.
Clue number three: "Towards the
distant mainland mountains, down
the beach, if you are pining for
treasure, it's within your
reach."
The third clue pretty much
pinpoints whether the rehidden
immunity idol is located.
I will need to share it with
Earl.
Hopefully one of us will find
it.
>> Yau-Man gave me a Ford F-350
2008.
I couldn't believe it.
Everything was so nice about the
truck, and it's all mine.
The other part of the reward is
to stop by and pick up a trailer
with, like, an office in it.
And then we go deliver a whole
bunch of school supplies to a
bunch of kids who really needed
the school supplies, you know.
>> I can't wait to see the look
on those children's faces.
>> I want to see the kids.
>> Me too.
( horn honking )
>> Come on, guys!
( cheering )
>> The big part of the reward
was giving a big box of school
supplies to these children and
these administrators at the
school, this very small school.
There was all kinds of stuff in
it.
There was sporting equipment,
school uniforms, jump ropes and
soccer balls, footballs.
Their faces just lit up.
That was just one of the most
amazing experiences I think I've
had in my life.
>> PROBST: Now we have something
for the teachers.
Come on over.
Thanks, Boo.
>> What we had for the teachers
was a mobile teachers' office.
( woman gasping )
>> It had a sofa in there, air
conditioning.
They had a computer, a copy
machine.
They had the best school around
now.
>> I think it will help
children.
It will lift the level of
achievement that they have, I
hope.
( laughter )
>> Boo, you blend in over there.
>> Dreamz, I'm from the USA,
America, a long ways away.
>> I like both of them.
It's warm here.
It's real cold over there.
You ever been to America?
>> No.
>> No?
This is my first time here.
It was a day that I'll remember
forever.
When I just got that brand-new
truck, it was my next step up.
And when these kids got this
stuff for the classroom, they
knew that was their next step
up.
I related to them 100%.
But I was thinking, when Yau-Man
gave me the car, what did he
gain out of that?
And then I thought about his
strategy.
If I give Yau-Man immunity off
my neck, I'm gone.
So the best thing for me to do
is to get rid of him before he
makes it to the final four.
>> Yeah.
What do you think?
>> I guess.
>> Yeah.
>> Pure strategy.
That truck was pure strategy.
It was a nice thing to do.
It was a real kind thing to do.
But the deal that Yau-Man set
up, he was actually trying to
accomplish getting rid of me
without literally saying, "Let's
get rid of Dreamz," because he
knows that me, Earl, and
Cassandra are going to stick
together and make it to the top
three.
I ain't going out like that.
I mean, not that I'm a snake or
nothing, but he let me realize
that this is a game, you know
what I mean?
If we make it to the final four
and I win immunity, I will give
Yau-Man the immunity necklace
because I appreciate what he did
for me, and I wouldn't want my
son to not be a man of his word.
That puts me in a bind of either
I got to get Yau-Man out of this
game before the final four or
lie and look like a total liar
and people not trust me again.
I know it sounds crazy, but we
got to play for us, take Yau-Man
out.
And if Earl get in the way, we
might have to take him out too,
but I doubt it.
I want to take Boo out before
Earl.
I still want to make it me, you,
and Earl to be top three.
>> You don't think it's
dangerous keeping Boo around
longer?
>> No.
...we have a couple of more
times to take out Boo, you know
what I mean?
>> Uh-huh.
It is tempting to consider
getting rid of Yau-Man.
He's a strong candidate, and I
think if he's in the number-one
or two position, he's going to
have quite a few of jury's votes
on his side.
Hey, Boo!
But Boo is a huge threat.
I mean, physically he's stronger
than Earl.
So I think, you know, if he
continues with winning immunity,
then he's a threat to our entire
alliance.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Yau-Man,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Yau-Man!
>> Yau.
( applause )
>> PROBST: Dreamz, since Yau-Man
wasn't with you, anything you
want to share about how nice
that Ford Super Duty rides?
>> Thank you, thank you, thank
you.
It was... it was lovely.
>> I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Keep enjoying it.
>> I think I will.
>> PROBST: Okay, you guys ready
to get to today's challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First thing's first.
Boo, I'll take back the immunity
necklace.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, all six
of you will start on a platform.
You will each have a ball
attached to a long rope.
Your goal is to throw the ball
through a hoop and pull down a
balance beam, which you will
then cross to the finish.
The first four to finish move on
to the next round, where we will
do it again.
The first two to finish move on
to the final round.
For the final round, you will
once again lower a balance beam.
This time when you cross the
beam, you will cross to a very
small perch, where you will use
a grappling hook to retrieve a
buoy out in the water.
First person to get their buoy
wins immunity.
We'll draw for spots, and we'll
get going.
First four to finish move on to
the next round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Dreamz having no trouble.
He hooks his balance beam and is
lowering it.
Dreamz is moving on.
Three more people moving on.
Cassandra throws her entire rope
and ball.
She's going to have to get in
and get wet to get it.
Yau-Man with a nice toss, just
misses.
Stacy not close.
Boo connects, lowering his
balance beam.
Earl connects, lowering his
Boo is across, joining Dreamz.
Earl needs to get across that
beam.
He barely makes it.
>> But I did.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, Boo, and Earl
are in the final.
We're looking for one more
person.
Cassandra taking a long time to
get back to her platform.
Yau-Man hooks his hoop.
Yau-Man, Dreamz, Boo, and Earl
moving on to the next round.
First two to finish move on to
the final round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Yau-Man loops his.
Dreamz just misses.
Yau-Man making his way across
the balance beam.
Hangs on.
Yau-Man moving on.
Boo lowers his balance beam.
Boo's got to get across.
Boo and Yau-Man moving on to the
final.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Boo almost falls off his
platform.
Yau-Man short.
Boo trying to lean it in.
Boo lowers his balance beam.
He's making his way across.
Boo now navigating a second
balance beam.
Boo is across to the perch.
Yau-Man, got to keep working.
Boo with the grappling hook now
has to retrieve the buoy.
That might do it.
Getting closer and closer.
Boo wins immunity!
Boo, come back over.
Boo once again safe at tribal
council.
Dreamz, Stacy, Cassandra, Yau-
Man, Earl, one of you going home
at the next tribal council.
Head on back to camp.
>> I might go get some wood.
>> Boo, boo.
>> I'm extremely stoked to win
immunity this time.
I think I noticed
disappointment, people talking
like "Okay, plan B" after I won
immunity.
So I'm not sure if that's the
case, but I was extremely happy
that I won.
>> I was wondering how you were
doing over there on Exile.
>> Good.
I did manage to stay dry.
>> When I came back to camp, I
had all three clues.
The third one pretty much
pinpoints where the rehidden
immunity idol is located.
As promised, I shared it with
Earl.
...and it's quotes...
>> It's a pine tree.
And it's hollow.
>> It's hollow.
So it's inside the hollow of a
pine tree.
>> Okay.
Inside the hollow of the pine
tree.
I'll be able to find it.
Yau-Man came back from Exile
Island with news.
So we're just hoping to find
that other hidden immunity idol,
and then Yau will have one, and
I will have one.
The first clue told me that it
was in a tree and easy to reach.
The second clue told me that it
was near a tower of rock.
How do I get up there?
And then, when I got the third
clue that it was a pine tree and
the hollow of a pine tree,
that's what did it.
So I started looking at pine
trees.
Oh!
( laughing )
Well, well, well.
There you go.
We are in business.
Yau and myself, we trust each
other 100%, and that's why we
are where we are now.
We have two idols, man.
Just think, we used to share an
idol, and now, go figure, we
both have our own immunity idol.
( laughter )
>> No, it was kind of hard.
It was... it was a lot of pine
trees.
>> You were gone a long time.
I was getting worried.
>> Yeah, I mean, I had...
>> I was hoping Boo didn't wake
up and ask me where you went.
Well, at this point, Earl and I
each have our own hidden
immunity idol.
With that, we will certainly
guarantee our place at the final
four, and with my deal I made
with Dreamz, I will guarantee
myself a place in the final
three.
>> This is the deal.
Yau's pretty smart, okay?
As you know, he wants me, him,
Earl, and Cassandra, which
knocks you out of the top four.
You get what I'm saying?
And that's not what I want to
do.
I want to get rid of Yau today.
We get rid of Yau today, you'll
be back in the top four.
You get what I'm saying?
You feeling me on this?
Yau has the immunity idol, so
he's going to use it in the top
five.
And then I give him my idol in
the top four.
So that puts him two spots up.
>> I was a little concerned that
I would be next today, but
Dreamz came up with another
idea.
He said if he wins immunity when
there's four people left, he
would give it to Yau-Man if Yau-
Man was still in the game.
So if Yau-Man is not in the
game, then, really, Dreamz
didn't go against him, you know,
in that deal.
So how many votes will be going
to Yau-Man?
>> Just you and me right now.
>> Hey.
>> Cassandra, any plan that I
planned hasn't worked out so
far.
Nothing that I planned worked so
far, because we always switched
it at the last minute, you know,
but we got to take Yau out.
If you ever want to help me, now
is the time.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I'm with Dreamz's plan.
I'm willing to do it.
>> Okay.
>> Are going to help me?
>> Yeah, I'm with the plan.
Yeah, I'm with you.
>> Are you going to help us?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Tonight's vote will be Yau-
Man.
>> So he won't even know what
hit him.
Make him think that Stacy's
going.
>> Yep.
>> Okay, all right.
There's definitely a risk
involved in voting Yau-Man.
The pros about it is that
looking down the line, if Yau-
Man is still in the game and he
makes it to one and two
position, that he'd be a
difficult competitor to beat.
The con is, though, that if he
uses the immunity, that I will
have burned two bridges, one
with Earl and one with Yau-Man,
and they're two valuable
bridges.
>> Can we talk to you for a
minute?
>> I mean, the key right now is
getting Yau-Man and Earl to
believe that they don't need to
use the immunity idol at this
point.
>> I don't think any of us did,
but I don't have any hard
feelings, you know.
Like, at this point, if Boo
didn't get immunity, it would be
smarter to remove him at this
point.
It's just who is the smarter
person to remove at which time?
That's all.
>> Kudos to Boo.
He saves himself.
So by default, it's Stacy.
Stacy already realized that
possibility and accepts her fate
and is going down with dignity.
She knows it's her time.
>> I can't do anything about the
numbers, you know?
Like, I cannot.
My hands are tied.
If I could, I would, but I
can't.
>> I like that.
I mean, I really, really respect
that.
>> Yeah.
>> I know.
At this point, you know, while
we're all planning to vote Stacy
out, I am still very much in
tune with what's going on around
me.
>> Yau?
>> Oh, please.
I had to make the best deal I
can with it.
Thanks for making the deal.
>> Look, I'm not dumb, Yau.
>> No.
>> I'm not dumb, I'm saying.
>> I know your strategy is to
take me out at three, and it's a
good strategy.
>> At this point, I'm quite sure
that people like Dreamz
certainly see me as a threat.
So far, in my conversation with
everybody, it seems to be still
all right.
But on the other hand, I will
never be 100% sure.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury: Rocky,
Lisi, Michelle, Edgardo, Mookie,
and Alex, voted out at the last
tribal council.
All right, at the reward
challenge, you were all playing
for a truck.
Yau-Man wins the truck and
immediately begins a negotiation
with you, Dreamz.
Tell me how that went down.
>> After Yau-Man won the truck,
he wanted to make an agreement.
He said if I make it to the
final four, and he's still
there, and I win immunity, to
give it to him.
And I was like, "Deal!"
You know, that's nothing to me.
So he gave me the truck.
I'm a great man of my word.
I owe Yau-Man to get the
immunity at final four, and I'm
going to see to it that I do get
it at final four.
>> PROBST: So, Yau-Man, what do
you expect from Dreamz in that
negotiation?
>> I expect Dreamz to live up to
his word.
It's a risk that he will renege
on it.
Certainly the bigger risk is
that the next two rounds there's
a big target on my back, so I
don't make it to the final four.
But I thought it's worth that
risk.
The other part also is Dreamz
needs the car, and that's my big
heart, let him have the car.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about the
hidden immunity idol.
It's come out that Yau-Man, at
least at one point, had it.
Who knows who has it now?
Boo, you worried?
>> It doesn't matter to me who
has it at this point.
>> PROBST: Cassandra, do you
believe that?
>> No, it definitely matters who
has the idol.
I mean, the idol can be used in
the next two tribal councils.
And I think that's critical to
the game, who has the idol.
>> PROBST: Million-dollar
blunder, Earl, if you have the
idol and don't play it and get
voted out.
>> You definitely have to gauge
when you're going to need it.
We're in the top six, so every
single time we come here, you're
a target.
There's no guarantees for
anything.
And now we got to start eating
each other, so that's when you
really start to worry.
>> PROBST: Stacy, how scared are
you tonight that it's you?
>> I'm worried just because I'm
a late-comer in this alliance,
and I think that before they
cannibalize each other, they may
want to try to get me out.
But I guess I'll find out
tonight.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, how about
you?
>> I'm definitely worried,
because me saying that I'll give
him the immunity idol at four,
people be like, "Oh, I can't let
him get to four."
I mean, so I would think Yau-Man
would try to protect me a little
bit until four, but you can
never tell.
You know, we haven't talked
about it.
>> PROBST: Stacy, what do you
think will be the result from
tonight's vote?
>> I think that everyone wants
to seem like they're playing
nice, but I think that there's
going to be lines drawn and
there's going to be division
amongst the tight-knit alliance,
because I don't think that it's
all going to be a vote one way
or the other.
I think it's going to be split.
>> PROBST: Well, there's
obviously a lot of uneasiness
surrounding this vote tonight.
If you have the idol and you
need to play it, you would
present it to me before I read
the votes.
Boo has individual immunity.
You can't vote for him.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Earl, you're up.
>> Good-bye, Stacy.
Sorry, it's your turn.
Good luck.
>> Sorry, bro, that's how the
game goes.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and feels they
need to play it, now is the time
to do so.
Yau-Man is playing the hidden
immunity idol.
Yau-Man's immune from tonight's
vote.
Any votes cast for Yau-Man do
not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Stacy.
Yau-Man.
That vote does not count.
One vote Stacy.
Stacy.
Two votes Stacy.
Yau-Man.
That vote does not count.
Stacy, you have two votes.
There are two votes left.
The best you can hope for is a
tie with another person.
Which means if this next vote is
for Yau-Man, you're going home.
It's Yau-Man.
13th person voted out and the
seventh member of our jury,
Stacy.
Stacy, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, there's still the
possibility that yet another
hidden immunity idol might come
into play.
The last time you can use it is
at the next tribal council.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, will Dreamz make it
to the final four and win
immunity?
>> My fate was sealed when I
took the truck.
>> PROBST: And if so, will he
honor his deal with Yau-Man?
>> I am an honorable person.
I am Dreamz.
>> PROBST: Join us for one of
the most tension-filled Survivor
finales ever.
>> Tonight I gambled.
I was hoping that Yau-Man
wouldn't pull out the hidden
immunity idol, which he did, and
I was outvoted.
I don't think I've ever been
tested in so many different
ways.
Making it 36 days is a big
accomplishment, and I hope that
I've made my friends and my
family proud.
I did my personal best and
definitely walk away with a big
smile.