>> PROBST: Previously on...
Survivor:
>> I slept really well last
night.
>> PROBST: From day one, a twist
in the game resulted in the Moto
Tribe living a privileged
lifestyle.
>> It's just going too great.
>> Yeah, it's, like, too good to
be true, man.
>> It's not even survival, it's
"thrival."
>> PROBST: While Ravu had next
to nothing.
>> Water!
>> Just lick some leaves, man.
>> I've never experienced
dehydration like this.
Half of us can't even stand up.
It's crazy.
(laughs): We're starving here,
bro.
>> PROBST: ...the disparity
between the two tribes helped
Moto go undefeated in the
challenges...
Dre scores for Moto!
...leading to animosity.
>> Why don't me and you go up
there right now.
>> We could.
>> Let's do that, then.
>> PROBST: Especially between
Rocky and James.
(indistinct shouts)
Moto wins reward!
>> This ain't the instant
dissolve coffee.
>> PROBST: Despite Moto's
comfort...
a game of politics was consuming
the tribe.
>> So if you guys know how to
make it, tell him how to make
it.
>> When we get into the merge,
me and Cassandra are gonna leave
and go with the other tribe.
>> PROBST: At Ravu...
>> You are driving me absolutely
insane.
>> PROBST: ...they were having
problems of their own.
You get all, like, sentimental
and sensitive.
You're a man: act like one.
Sitting around dealing with
somebody, you really can't tell
him how you feel because you're
worried about his vote.
Right now I could care less
about his vote.
>> Truthfully, I go out, I'm
just lip gloss, good to go.
>> PROBST: And no one could
escape Rocky's short fuse.
>> Rita is basically wanting me
take my T-shirt and hang myself
from a palm tree.
>> PROBST: And we are tied,
six-six.
At the last immunity challenge,
it was as close as ever.
Yau-Man, trying to remember.
But a couple of fatal
mistakes...
Yau-Man makes his selection, and
it is wrong.
Rocky could win it for Ravu
right here.
...sealed Ravu's fate.
No match.
Moto wins immunity!
With Ravu heading back to Tribal
Council...
>> Anthony okay with you, then?
>> It's fine.
>> Anthony okay with you?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> All right?
>> PROBST: It came down to
Anthony or Rita.
>> Well, Rita's running her
mouth all day, guy.
Rita's got to go.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council...
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji...
...Anthony escaped the vote, and
Rita was sent home.
Rita, the tribe has spoken.
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
♪ ♪
(flies buzzing)
>> These freakin' flies, man,
where did that come from?
Didn't used to be like this.
>> Today's day 15.
I'm very surprised I'm still in
the tribe.
Uh, I guess I dodged a big
bullet this last round when I
screwed up on the, uh, immunity
challenge, and I'm glad my head
was not on the chopping block.
People like me don't have that
much to offer in terms of the
strength and power component,
and so I think if it comes down
to who is the most dispensable,
then, you know, I'm definitely
one of the candidates.
>> Take it out?
>> Okay.
Let's see what we have.
Ooh, it's heavy.
>> Oh.
>> It's not socks.
"Today no brawn required.
Some brain-teasing at the least.
When it's over, one gets exiled,
while others get to feast."
>> Nice, bro.
>> So we just got tree mail,
and we're excited about tree
mail because today tree mail is
all about brainteasers and food.
>> PROBST: Come on in.
Moto getting your first look at
the new Ravu Tribe.
Rita voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
How's everybody doing?
>> Pretty good.
>> Good.
>> PROBST: Need one person from
each tribe.
Pick a spot right over here.
Edgardo for Moto.
Earl for Ravu.
Everybody, drop your butts.
We are choosing new tribes.
>> (whispers): What?!
(theme song playing)
>> PROBST: The tribes of
Moto and Ravu as you knew them
are no more.
Let's get to it.
Earl and Edgardo volunteered to
step forward.
You two will start the new tribe
selection.
The rest of you will alternate.
When selecting a member, you
must choose somebody from the
other tribe.
And because there's an odd
number of people, one person
will not be selected on either
tribe.
Moto, because you have the
numbers advantage, you've earned
the right to select first.
You are choosing somebody from
the Ravu tribe.
>> Mookie.
>> PROBST: Rivals become tribe
mates now.
Earl, somebody from Moto.
>> Boo.
>> PROBST: Boo joins Earl.
Mookie.
>> Alex.
>> PROBST: Alex joins Mookie and
Edgardo.
Boo.
>> Michelle.
>> PROBST: Michelle joins Boo
and Earl.
Alex.
>> Rocky.
>> PROBST: Rocky joins Alex,
Mookie and Edgardo.
>> Wow.
They're looking strong.
>> PROBST: Michelle.
>> I'll take Cassandra.
>> PROBST: Michelle chooses
Cassandra to join herself, Boo,
and Earl.
Rocky, your choice.
>> Come on, Dreamz.
See if you can work this out,
baby.
>> PROBST: Maybe the biggest
rivalry thus far in Survivor:
Fiji just paired up.
Dreamz joins Alex, Mookie,
Edgardo and his new friend,
Rocky.
Cassandra.
>> Yau-Man.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man joins
Cassandra, Earl, Michelle, and
Boo.
Dreamz, you have only one
choice.
You have to choose somebody from
the old Ravu.
That person is Anthony.
Anthony joins a tribe consisting
only of men at this point.
Yau-Man, last tribe member to be
selected on these two tribes.
Who you gonna take?
>> Stacy.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man takes Stacy.
Lisi, never good to be odd
person out.
You are, however, still in the
game.
>> Aw, geez!
(laughing)
>> PROBST: Were you worried?
>> No. I thought this would be,
like, I'm out.
Now would be a good time to
exit.
>> PROBST: Well, so I guess you
just told these guys that you're
fine going home.
>> All I'm saying is that I
wouldn't mind, you know...
saying, "Okay, great, guys, do
your business."
>> PROBST: Well, for the time
being, you're still in this
game.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: You'll be going to
Exile Island.
>> Oh, geez! Thanks.
That's just great.
That's just great. Thanks.
>> PROBST: But maybe a little
time on Exile... to straighten
out your head, you'll come back
wanting to play.
The good news, Lisi, whether you
think so or not, you won't be
going to Tribal Council, which
means you can't be voted out.
You will return after the next
Tribal Council and join
whichever tribe did go to Tribal
and had to vote somebody out.
Also, there is another clue to
the whereabouts of a hidden
Immunity Idol.
Perhaps you'll find it, won't
want it, we'll give it to
somebody who does.
>> (laughs)
>> PROBST: Boat's waiting for
you.
>> Great. Thanks.
Uh, bye, guys.
>> PROBST: Okay, one very big
decision left to make.
Which group is going to live on
the luxurious Moto Beach...
>> We are.
>> We'll take that.
>> PROBST: ...and which group of
people's going back to Ravu.
Edgardo, take a step forward.
Earl, take a step forward.
Here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna take both these buffs.
You two are gonna
rock-paper-scissor to see who
gets the right to reach in and
select.
>> All right, Earl.
>> All right.
>> One, two, three.
>> PROBST: Paper covers rock.
Edgardo earns the right to
choose.
>> 50-50.
Do it.
>> PROBST: If Edgardo pulls out
a green buff, that means you
guys are all going back to the
lap of luxury.
If Edgardo pulls out the orange
buff, you're gonna be tested at
Ravu Camp.
You ready?
>> I'll go with my right hand.
>> Go ahead and grab that
orange.
>> PROBST: Show it.
(whooping)
Here's the rest of your buffs.
>> Don't sweat it, Eddie.
Don't sweat it.
We'll make it up.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, Michelle,
Earl, life's gonna change.
You're going to Moto Beach.
Here are the rest of your buffs.
Waiting for both of you back at
your new homes is a little
housewarming gift.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: For those of you who
have been to Exile Island, those
clues are still in play just
like they always were.
Grab your stuff, guys.
Head on back to your new home.
♪ ♪
>> Clue number six.
"The highest point,
the jutting point,
the edge of the lip, below.
Dig, dig, dig and save yourself
from the fatal blow."
Yeah. Whatever.
After the team split, yeah, I
pretty much had a fit.
I had a cushy alliance.
I felt like my comfort zone was
yanked.
I thought I was going home.
I'm, like, whoo-hoo!
And, all of a sudden, Jeff is,
like, "You're going to Exile
Island."
And I got pissed.
I wish I would have just stopped
for a minute and let things soak
in, but I'm more of an abrasive
character.
Dude, I can't change who I am.
You either take me or you put me
on Exile Island.
>> Moto, baby, welcome home!
(whooping, indistinct talking)
>> What do we got, Earl?
>> Look at Earl.
(indistinct talking, whooping)
>> No way, don't get in the bed
dirty, Earl!
>> Don't get in the bed dirty.
>> Ah...
Life at Team Moto is better than
ridiculous, it's ridonkulous.
Garcon!
My breakfast.
Nothing, everything.
I-I like ev... I think I'll go
with everything.
>> Hey, guys, y'all sit down.
Let's go.
Get y'all a plate.
>> Y'all eat, y'all serve your
own selves first.
>> Eat slow so you don't, you
know, you don't get sick.
>> This is real food. Man!
>> Oh, this is good cheese.
>> Anything is good at this
point.
>> I'm trying to just, like,
keep myself contained.
>> After I survey the land and
look at the situation a little
more, um, I will be looking for
the Immunity Idol.
Yau and I have an upper hand,
'cause we're the only ones that
know about Exile Island and the
clues and what's going on.
So I am not worried, not at all,
about someone else trying to
find the idol, 'cause they have
no idea that it's even on this
island.
(chattering and whooping)
>> I'm gonna have a mimosa.
>> Oh, a mimosa?
Don't you dare have a hangover.
>> Guys, cheers.
>> Yummy.
>> To the new Moto.
>> OTHERS: To the new Moto.
>> New Moto.
>> Moto-licious, baby.
>> Oh, my God, let's eat!
Let's eat!
>> Big morale went up.
Don't let this morale go down.
>> Well, I'll tell you, it's
rough out here.
>> I want to say something,
though.
There was two choices-- either
had that tribe over there...
>> Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it.
>> No, no, no, but I'm saying,
like, we're gonna be way
stronger in challenges, and if
tomorrow we have a challenge, we
kick ass, man.
>> Yeah.
>> We're gonna kick some ass.
It's men now.
(several talking)
>> Men! Yeah!
>> Showing up here, you know,
it's really not that bad.
>> Whoa!
>> Yeah, I had a strong
alliance-- it was Boo, Stacy,
Lisi and myself-- um, but I
always felt there was kind of a
power struggle.
The girls were difficult to
predict.
I wasn't sure where Boo stood
half the time.
So being in a tribe where I feel
like, you know, we're all
gung-ho, we're all warriors,
we're ready to take these guys
on, I'm very happy with it.
(whooping)
And this may sound weird, but,
like, I'm glad that there are no
women here, man.
The women are just politics
and it's just, like...
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> That's why... that's why
every person that's been voted
off has been a woman, you know
what I mean?
>> It's just, like, I was
getting so sick of dealing with
them.
>> I-I only need to ask one
question.
How was Sylvia in camp, man?
(laughter)
>> Shoot myself in the face...
>> That's why she was out.
>> Just excited to, you know, be
eating, hanging out with some of
the boys.
No offense, I love women, I love
'em, I love to touch 'em and
make out and have conversations
with 'em, get along well.
But, uh, you know, in this type
of environment, this type of
game, you don't need any, like,
stupid, like, girl stories or
distractions or any stupid
things like that.
>> There's a little quote that
gets me through, like, a lot of,
like, rough times.
I don't know if you ever seen
The Count of Monte Cristo, the
movie.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> It starts out, there's a line
in it that goes, um... "Life is
a storm, my young friends.
One day you're battered in the
sunlight, and you're shattered
on the rocks the next.
But it's what you do when that
storm comes that makes you a
man.
So shout, do your worst, for I
shall do mine, and the fates
will know you as a man."
>> Yeah.
>> I remember that scene.
That scene was awesome, too.
We'll say that every time we go
to a challenge.
(laughter)
>> Yeah, we have different
strategies, my friend, but I
assure you, the result is the
same.
>> Yes.
(thunder rumbles)
>> What's going on?
Yeah, what's the situation out
here?
(indistinct conversation)
>> We have tons of coconuts,
tons of crabs.
So we go crabbing and snails.
>> We should light a fire before
that, or...?
>> Yeah, light a fire, get one
going, and then go fishing and
catch some hermit crabs.
>> You want to have Anthony just
get the fire going and we'll go
fishing or...?
>> Yeah. If you don't mind,
Anthony?
>> Is that cool?
>> All right, let's do it.
>> Hey, let's all grab some wood
on the way back, though.
>> All right.
>> Cool.
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
>> So, there's this time in
everybody's life, in high
school, that first gym class,
when everybody has to go take
that first shower afterwards,
when nobody really wants to take
their shirt off, except for the
guys who know that they're cut.
I'm a nerd; I know this.
I'm a nerd, I'm a geek, I'm a
dweeb, or whatever the hell you
want to call it.
I have been for forever.
This is the burly man team, and
right now I'm obviously the
weakest person in the tribe,
and, um, I got my work cut out
for me.
I am so screwed right now.
Uh...
wow.
(bat screeches)
(chittering)
>> We're gonna have to go with
these.
>> Yeah.
>> So we'll use that line.
I think that's the thinnest
line.
I'm gonna use these two.
>> Yeah, there's two more...
>> This switch threw a couple
of roadblocks into my million,
but this game is full of
roadblocks.
I was counting my million.
(laughs)
I had it tight, my plan was
tight, but it's changed.
It might come full circle if
things work out like I want.
We'll see.
>> Hopefully, we can have some
fish, potatoes and rice for
breakfast.
Is that a nice, big, energetic
breakfast with some coffee?
>> Uh-huh.
>> There's three old Moto and,
uh, three old Ravu on the new
Team Moto that I started.
And I know that makes Boo a
little nervous.
So I know the game is really
beginning.
They're gonna try to get a swing
vote... from somebody.
But everything is gonna have to
go through me. Everything.
My plan was always to have your
friends close and your enemies
closer.
>> Earl.
>> Delivery service.
>> (laughs): It's not much.
I got you guys a little shot
each.
>> Thank you, ma'am.
>> You're welcome.
(sighs): Ah.
>> Wow, coffee!
>> This place is definitely
positive for me than the last
camp.
I felt, as far as alliances, I
was on the out.
I like Earl a lot.
I like, um, Yau-Man a lot.
You know, I'm a free agent right
now.
I'm really just gonna try to see
how the cards fold over the next
couple of days.
>> Cassandra, do you think Boo
feels nervous?
>> Oh, very. He had a lot of
allies on the other team.
>> It's a different chemistry
and dynamic now, so...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> You could be a swing vote.
>> I know.
>> You could change everything.
>> Oh, I know.
>> And Boo could be gone.
>> I know.
>> Just like that.
>> Mm-hmm. (laughs)
>> A word or two here and
there in the right situation,
you paint the picture the right
way, she could be right on my
side.
Appreciate you bringing the
coffee.
>> Sure, sure.
You guys keep fishing.
>> Yeah, we're trying to do
something.
>> (laughs)
>> It'd be nice to have a little
meat.
I have Yau-Man, I have Michelle.
They're all about the team.
All you need is that one vote,
and then who has all the power
then?
That would be me.
>> I got my work cut out for me.
'Cause right now I guess I've
replaced Yau-Man as the fire
tender and the water tender.
And right now I feel pretty
alone.
I got nobody to trust.
I have absolutely no one to
trust over here.
And... I got to see if I can
change that.
But unfortunately, I'm left back
here at the homestead to tend
the fires, while... the big men
go off and Cookie's still here
at the campfire.
>> Look at this, man.
Look at all these...
Hey, Rocky, come here.
>> What's that?
>> Look at all these crabs.
>> I'll hold the stick up here
and I'll shove 'em off.
>> That's your shell, buddy.
>> Ooh!
>> He's right there.
>> Oh, oh, oh!
>> He's right here.
He's right here.
Step on him.
>> You like that, don't you,
crab?
>> Hey, hey, hey.
>> I mean, what I felt these
guys needed-- um, Anthony, Rocky
and Mookie-- they just needed a
kick-start.
Now, food notwithstanding, these
are men that I think are true
competitors, and if I was losing
every single time, I mean, I
mean, that would definitely do
something to my psyche.
>> Wait, so how is Anthony
holding up?
Is he doing all right?
>> He's doing all right.
>> I'm not gonna say...
He looked a little flustered at
some of those challenges.
>> Uh, he's a little effeminate.
You know?
>> There's nothing wrong with
that.
>> No, no, I'm not saying that
anything's wrong with it, it's
just, you know... sometimes it's
hard for him to carry his own
weight.
>> Who-who... If y'all had three
people going to merge, who would
it have been?
>> I mean... all strategy
changes, you know what I mean?
>> Yeah. It's crazy now.
Everything is crazy now.
>> There's a lot of crab...
Coming into this, it's
three-three.
Majority rules always in
Survivor.
So I knew that I needed to bring
in one person from the other
tribe.
Rocky, I don't know very well,
but I know he doesn't get along
with Dreamz, and I know he's
sort of a volatile personality.
Anthony does not strike me as a
particularly strong player in
this game.
And Mookie and I had clicked
before, and I knew it would be
in Mookie's best interest to
join up with us.
>> But, oh, a huge fish.
Right there, right there, Mook.
Mook, look at it!
>> Got him.
>> You got him.
>> Oh, a huge fish!
Yeah, baby!
>> Oh, we gonna feast, baby!
Oh, yeah!
How is this?
>> Can we eat this guy?
He's so ugly.
>> Yeah, but we gonna eat him.
>> He's ugly.
>> Ugly.
>> (laughing)
>> How can we eat this?
We got the big boy.
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
>> We did it.
>> Whoo!
>> (clamoring)
>> I'll be honest, I-I was
pretty upset that we were going
back here again to nothing, but,
um, to get a fish?
I mean, that just does so much
psychologically and mentally.
Now you know you can get fish.
Now you know you can get food.
And these guys, they came from
Moto, are really positive and
they brought life, new life to
Ravu.
>> Who's happy?
>> Wow!
Wow!
>> It's like your first time,
isn't it?
>> That's right.
>> They caught five fish in less
than two hours.
Big, huge fish, with teeth.
It's over.
It is over.
The bad times are about to go.
I think we're going to do big
things.
I think we're going to, I think
we're going to rock.
>> That's for sure, man.
>> Ravu!
>> Ravu, baby!
>> Right now, on paper, we're a
superpower.
A superpower.
I said it again.
We look good.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to your
first challenge as new tribes?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, let's do it, baby.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Michelle.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
Today's challenge is going to
test how effectively you
communicate with your new
tribe mates.
Each tribe will be belted in to
a large, six-point, sliding hub.
By shifting, sliding and
adjusting each other, you're
going to maneuver through a
field of bamboo poles.
As you go, you must pass
through five gates.
Making things more difficult,
the tribe paths intersect, which
means the two tribes could and
probably will collide before you
reach the finish line.
The first tribe to get all
their members across the finish
line wins immunity.
Guaranteed at least one more
day in this game.
Losers, Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody will be voted out.
Everything clear?
>> Yup.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Give you a minute to
strategize, we'll get started.
Here we go.
It is the new Moto taking on
the new Ravu.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
This challenge is all about
communicating, how well you
work together.
>> Okay, y'all slide.
>> Wait, wait.
>> Go slide, slide.
Go slide, slide.
>> PROBST: Working their way
through their first gate.
Ravu has cleared their first
gate.
>> Okay, move forward, Ed.
This way.
>> PROBST: Michelle getting
stuck in the middle of Ravu's
hub.
A bit of a standstill.
Moto gonna let Ravu have this.
>> Climb on, quick.
>> Twist.
Start to twist.
>> Move back.
>> Watch out, watch out!
>> All right, come on.
>> That way, that way, that way.
>> Move up, move up, move up.
>> Both of them, man.
>> Go through.
>> Go, go, Dreamz. Go.
>> PROBST: Ravu is through
their second gate.
Moto approaching their second
gate.
>> There you go.
Okay, I'm in.
>> PROBST: Moto now through
their second gate.
Ravu with a bit of a lead.
>> Cassandra, back up.
Come in, Cassandra.
>> Come in, Yau. Come in, Yau.
>> Come in, Yau-Man.
>> There you go.
We're doing good, baby.
>> Come back, come back, come
back.
>> Dreamz, move forward.
Move this forward.
You've got clearance.
>> PROBST: Ravu halfway through
gate three.
Moto at their third gate.
>> Good job!
>> Okay. Go, Yau. Go, Yau, and
we all twist. All twist.
Ravu. All clear.
>> Okay, I'm through.
>> PROBST: Moto is through
their third gate.
Ravu is through their third
gate.
Michelle once again wedged
inside the spinning hub of Ravu.
>> Go. Push.
>> PROBST: Ravu pushing hard
against Moto.
>> Michelle, go on top, go on
top of it.
>> Stop there?
>> PROBST: Michelle trying to
maneuver over Ravu's pole.
>> All right. Fine. Go under.
>> Just stay here. Back up.
>> Everybody?
>> Come on, Yau! Come on!
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Push! Push!
>> PROBST: Nobody wants to give
an inch with immunity on the
line.
>> There you go.
>> Come on.
>> Come on, Yau.
>> PROBST: Ravu completely tied
up in the spinning hub of Moto.
>> All right, come on in, babe.
>> PROBST: Strange game of
Twister taking place.
>> (groaning)
>> Pull back.
You gotta pull it in.
>> Hold on.
We need him through first.
And he's under.
>> Run.
>> PROBST: Now Moto's free to
move on.
>> Mookie, Mookie, back up.
>> PROBST: After a big impasse,
this challenge is back on.
>> And pull, and pull, and pull.
>> PROBST: Both tribes at their
fourth gate.
>> Back up, back up.
>> Right here, right here!
In the ring.
>> PROBST: Moto is through
their fourth gate.
>> We're through!
>> Come forward, come forward,
come forward.
>> PROBST: Ravu now through
their fourth gate.
We are neck and neck with one
gate left!
>> No, under it.
>> No, under it!
>> Go!
PROBST: Michelle, blocking Ravu.
Moto trying to steal the lead.
>> Go back!
No, the other way, the other
way.
Push, push through.
Now get on the outside.
Go, go, go, go.
Yau, come in, Yau.
>> PROBST: Dreamz now the one
stuck in the middle.
>> Pull!
(all shouting)
>> Hold up!
Aw!
>> PROBST: The challenge has
become very physical.
Nobody wants to go home tonight.
>> Get that pole.
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: You are going to
have to work this out.
A major roadblock.
We are dead even.
>> Ow!
>> Come on, take it, man!
>> Okay, let me in.
Okay.
>> PROBST: They've worked it
out.
Ravu now back on the move.
Moto on the move.
>> Other side, other side!
>> PROBST: Ravu at their fifth
gate.
Both tribes trying to maneuver
through a very narrow
passageway on that fifth gate.
>> You can go through, Alex.
>> PROBST: Ravu jammed up.
Moto with a chance to catch up.
>> Back up!
>> Come through.
>> PROBST: Moto making a little
progress.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Ravu making some
progress.
>> Come through.
Let him go first.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man is through.
Boo is through. Michelle is
through.
Earl is through.
Cassandra the last member to
get through the fifth gate.
Moto has cleared their fifth
gate.
They're heading per the finish.
>> Go, go.
>> PROBST: Ravu has cleared
their fifth gate.
They're heading for the finish.
We're neck and neck as we go to
the finish.
Stacy is across the line for
Moto.
Everybody's got to be across
the finish line.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Alex now across for
Ravu.
It's going to be very close!
Moto closer.
>> Turn, turn!
>> Get back, get back!
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Moto wins immunity!
>> Whoo!
>> Yeah!
>> That's the way to hold it
together, team.
>> Way to be strong.
Way to be strong.
>> PROBST: Moto...
congratulations.
As a tribe, still Moto is
undefeated.
You are safe tonight.
Ravu, great effort.
Unfortunately, same result.
Ravu still winless.
Tribal Council tonight.
One of the six of you is going
home.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp, see you at Tribal.
>> I got strength now to carry
the flag.
>> So we lost the challenge
again.
And now old Cookie has been
left by the fire to tend the
fire and make the water while
the boys go out hunting and
fishing.
So I'm a little bit in panic
mode right now.
Cinderella, a black, male
Cinderella.
What kind of whacked-out stuff
is that?
Can I go fishing with the boys?
No.
You can't tell underneath this
calm demeanor, but right now
Anthony is a turmoil of waves
and emotions and worried sick
that he's getting voted out
tonight.
>> Like I said, bro, we made it
this far.
I don't know how.
I'm serious, guys.
Like, I like him.
He's a good kid.
You know, he's not a bad guy.
But, like...
So you gotta go backwards
before you go forward
sometimes, buddy.
Philosophy in the ocean today.
>> I can tell you now if they
bring up a name, it's probably
going to be me.
>> Anthony talked to me today.
He wanted me to tell him if it
is him or not, which I don't
know if I'm going to do that
either because I pretty much
know that it's either going to
be him or Rocky, so...
I think Rocky should go because
he's so emotionally driven and
he's lazy.
He don't do nothing around the
camp.
Anthony makes the water, you
know; he keeps the fire going.
But Anthony being weaker than
Rocky in challenges is
probably going to have a lot of
effect on the rest of the team.
>> You know, Rocky's got a lot
of emotion.
He's got a lot of heart.
Sometimes he blows up, man.
>> You are right about that.
>> And I can tell you that
caused a whole lot of headache.
>> I see.
>> Mook, help me with this real
quick.
So I don't... I don't put out
the fire.
>> Ow!
I just burned my foot!
>> Come on!
>> Chill out.
>> See what I'm saying, Mook.
That's why I wanted you to help
me out, bro.
>> Anthony!
>> Rocky has a few screws loose
in his head.
>> Yeah!
Huh!
It's over!
>> He yells at people and tells
people what to do.
I noticed that since I got in
here.
>> Anthony!
Which is the drinking water?
>> I mean, Anthony is his
little bitch.
"Anthony, make the water.
Anthony, put the fire."
>> Put another log on the fire
there, Anthony?
>> I see myself really far
from, from being friends, or
liking Rocky a lot.
>> Oh, this food thing...
I might have to eat my
portion of bread and cheese,
bro.
>> And I wouldn't want him
making the merger because all he
would cause is a lot of turmoil
and you know, a mess.
>> So I don't know, man.
I talked to Alex, and he told
me he didn't know who he was
going to vote for yet because
of the...
Of the Rocky situation.
>> The thing is, Rocky's really
bold though.
Rocky's really bold.
>> But, uh...
>> Watch out, man.
>> I'm going to break something.
>> Just a bit harsh...
>> No, I mean, I'll tell you the
truth, man.
My vote right now, it will be
50-50 right now between and you
Rocky.
So, but I mean, this is...
That's my decision, man, and
it's not going to change until
we get there, so...
>> It's all good.
>> Am I going to miss Anthony
when he's gone?
We had a couple of good times,
you know, when we started like
not really...
Not really, no.
If he had a drop of social
skills, it might-- it might
make this decision hard.
But he hasn't had any since day
one.
Anthony, where is the flint?
And then when he tries to,
like, finagle his way through
things, he has to go
like, go around-- no offense--
like a girl.
Like a little female.
( whining ) Whining and trying
to work on your sympathy.
You know what I mean?
It doesn't work.
>> PROBST: Edgardo, tell me your
first impressions when you got
to Ravu Beach and saw your new
home.
>> I thought it was going to be
a worse place, you know, no
crabs, no anything.
So I was like, you know, for 15
days it wasn't even really,
like you know, trying to
survive, so in my mind I was
like now I'm going to actually
start playing Survivor.
>> PROBST: Mookie, tell me
about today.
After you're done talking
about the challenge, you got
to get back to life, right?
>> Yeah, we got back from the
challenge, and right away we're
hungry, so Dreamz and Rocky,
Edgardo, Alex and I go out
fishing over on some other part.
Anthony is working the fire,
boiling some water, filling up
the canteens.
Everyone is doing everything,
you know, so it's... it's
pretty good.
>> PROBST: So, Anthony, does it
concern you at all that with
Tribal Council looming, the
entire tribe is somewhere else,
and you're boiling water?
>> You know, I'm not going to
lie.
I was concerned.
I mean, you don't know what
everybody else is saying
because you're isolated, but
you do what you get assigned to
do.
>> To be honest with you,
Anthony, this is the best
advice I can give you.
Put your cards on the table.
If you're upset the way you're
getting treated, you got to put
your foot down and say,
"Hey, guy, you know, I don't
mind doing the fire.
I need help real quick and
then do what you want."
Let people know what's going
through your mind.
Because if you don't tell them,
how are they going to know?
You know what I mean?
No one's a mind reader.
At least I'm not.
I don't know about you boys.
So maybe if you take some of
those words and you can use
them later on in your life or
tomorrow or the next day or ten
minutes from now, whenever you
want to, you know what I mean?
>> PROBST: Anthony, pretty
candid advice, and still,
you're just sitting there.
What is so hard for you about
speaking up and owning your own
space?
>> You know, I tried to own my
space early on, and, you know
what, I got... I got knocked
back.
>> You can't give up, bro.
You can't give up.
>> Who says I gave up?
>> You get knocked back, you
stand up and take another knock
in the mouth.
You can't back down from
nobody at any point in time in
your life 'cause you won't get
respect.
That's the problem.
>> Rock, let me tell you...
>> I'm trying to help you out.
I'm giving a life lesson here,
buddy.
>> I'm going to tell you the
truth-- the only person that I
really have not felt I've gotten
any respect from has really been
you.
>> No, guy, you got to
respect... first you got to
comfortable...
>> I do respect myself.
>> You have to be comfortable
in your own skin.
You're not.
You can't sit up here and tell
these people how you feel or
back at camp or anything like
that.
You have poor social skills.
>> Oh, I got poor social skills?
>> You have poor social
skills, bro, yes!
>> Dude, Please, please, please,
Rocky.
>> I'm not going to debate with
you.
I'm trying to help you out.
>> Do you know anything about
me?
>> No, because you don't tell
me nothing, bro.
>> Have you asked?
Have you asked me?
>> Please don't raise your
voice in my ear.
No, guy, here's the thing:
I talk to people who talk to me;
I sit down like men.
>> You're talking I'm not a
man again.
>> I didn't say that.
Grow a spine, bro.
>> You've done it before, Rocky.
>> Seriously, like a jellyfish.
Toughen up.
I don't know what's going on in
your mind, guy, but you act
like a little girl sometimes,
okay?
You're effeminate.
>> Oh, I'm effeminate.
>> Extremely effeminate, yes.
>> I'm sorry, please.
>> Toughen up, toughen up.
>> No, no, no.
>> Toughen up.
>> This is why I don't say
anything.
>> Keep going, man!
Fight for what's yours!
Take the skirt off a little
bit; let's go!
>> PROBST: Alex, why were your
hands buried in your head.
Why is this bad?
>> You know, I was thinking to
myself, wow, that is some tough
love.
I feel bad because I think what
he said might have hurt
Anthony's feelings.
To be honest, that would hurt
my feelings.
So I just felt bad for the guy.
And that's... all I felt was
empathy, that's it.
>> PROBST: Anthony, Rocky could
easily just kiss your ass and
say you're a good guy,
Anthony, don't worry about it,
and write your name down.
What are you feeling right now?
>> I appreciate all of the
advice about standing up for
myself.
What I don't appreciate is the
name-calling.
>> PROBST: Do you want to be in
this game?
>> Yes, I want to be in this
game!
You know why I want to be in
this game?
Because I worked for so much.
I've popped myself, hurt myself
in these challenges.
I held back from myself for
giving people of myself, I held
back from giving Rock of myself.
You know why I haven't said
anything?
'Cause I want to make sure
that the team works so we can
win a freaking challenge.
I was trying to keep people
cool, keep people calm, keep
people happy, but you know what,
screw that.
If it means I have to piss
people off to stay here, which
doesn't make any friggin' sense
to me, then fine, so be it.
But I'm here, all right?
I'll be brutally honest with
people.
But I need to be here.
I deserve to be here.
I want it.
And if you guys want it, you
need it, you want to keep me
here because I'll help you get
there.
Oh, I'll help you get there.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Mookie, you're up.
>> I was getting respect back
before you got... man.
And, uh... watch your mouth.
>> It's time to go.
I don't know, I hope you can
take this experience and learn
from it, and I think you'll be
all right if you can do that.
Have a good one, buddy.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Rocky.
>> Huh.
>> PROBST: Anthony.
One vote Rocky,
one vote Anthony.
Anthony.
Two votes Anthony.
That's three votes Anthony.
One vote Rocky.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji: Anthony.
That's four; that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Anthony, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Well, tomorrow, Lisi
joins this tribe as a new
member.
The job you do in welcoming her
will certainly have a big
impact on how well this tribe
does.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Welcome home, baby.
>> PROBST: Lisi joins the Ravu
boys' club.
>> Back at Moto I didn't like
her and she didn't like me.
So she should be worried.
>> Bye, Yau.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man continues to
search for the hidden idol.
>> I'm always the target but if
I have the immunity idol, I
can go quite far.
>> PROBST: And things get rough.
>> Follow that ramp...
>> I'm a little pissed off.
I'm a lot pissed off.
I'm mad at myself for
apparently not screaming to the
world, being a jerk.
That's what you need to prove
that you're out for a million
dollars.
Regardless of what Rocky says,
I have great social skills.
I'm not what was wrong with
that tribe.
It was Mookie and James.
Those are the problem with Ravu
and that's why they're losing.
They're going to continue to
lose until both those guys are
gone.