>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> You're driving me absolutely
insane.
>> PROBST: At Ravu, Rocky blew
up at Anthony.
>> You're getting all, like,
sentimental and sensitive.
You're a man.
Act like one.
>> They want me out of this
game, they're going to have push
me off, because there's no way
in hell I'm giving up.
>> PROBST: At the Moto camp, an
unspoken alliance of five
emerged.
>> The five musketeers.
>> From the beginning, there has
been a bond between Boo, Alex,
Edgar, myself, and Stacy.
All we know is that the five of
us get along.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
>> Lisi, let's go, baby.
>> PROBST: Moto's strategy is
starting to work.
...Moto continued to perform
well...
( cheering )
Moto wins reward!
...intensifying the gap between
the wealthy...
>> PROBST: Fish, rice, and a
king-sized bed.
...and the destitute.
>> What happened?
>> We lost, bro!
What do you mean, "What
happened?"
>> PROBST: Yau-Man was sent to
Exile Island, where he learned
the idol was back at camp.
>> "It's buried under the
highest point of the big cave."
I'm quite sure I know where the
idol is.
>> I can't function like this.
>> PROBST: Moto suffered its
first blow...
>> All right, Gary, I'm going to
call in the medical boat now and
get you out of here.
>> PROBST: ...when Gary was
forced to leave the game.
At the immunity challenge...
Ravu has a lot of time to make
up.
...Ravu could not change their
luck, and Moto once again
claimed victory.
Motto wins immunity, still
undefeated!
But a message in a bottle left
Moto with a dilemma.
>> "You must now decide which is
more important to you."
>> PROBST: Moto had to choose
between giving up immunity or
their camp of comfort.
>> Jeff, we're keeping our
comfort and going to tribal
council.
>> PROBST: Back at camp, the
alliance of five solidified.
>> We need to put in our votes
and make a decision.
>> I vote Liliana.
>> I vote Liliana too.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji...
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: ...Liliana was blind-
sided.
Liliana, the tribe has spoken.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> You guys like it well-done,
right?
Medium-well, all right.
I just came back from Exile
Island.
The clues to the whereabouts of
the immunity idol definitely
points to the fact that it's in
our tribal camp area.
In fact, it's very specific that
it is at the threshold of our
cave, where we are sleeping.
It's very frustrating.
I sort of know where it is, and
I don't know how to get to it.
>> Earl is the only other person
who has been to Exile Island.
>> He knows that I know where it
is sort of, and I know he knows
sort of where it is.
So maybe at some point, we can
join forces in finding this
idol.
>> He has all the clues, and I
only have a couple, but he's
going to need my help.
>> I like Yau.
I just want to build that trust
with him, okay?
"Yau, you can trust me.
I have your back."
Just when it comes down to it,
me just helping him get the idol
is just a good move.
( theme song playing )
>> We're struggling right now,
and all of us are starving.
The other camp, they have a
shelter, a king-sized mattress,
tons of food, fishing gear.
We're still sleeping on palm
fronds.
We at least got a good water
system going.
And that's about it.
>> Yau-Man and I had a little
chat about the idol.
I mean, he has an idea where it
might be, but there's no way for
him to look for it when people
are there, because the idol is
actually in our little cave.
So we got to get people out of
there.
It's time to go hunting for
crab-- crab, snails, anything
you see-- if you want to eat.
>> I'm very excited.
I got a chance to dig, I don't
know for how long.
The problem is I don't know when
they will show up.
I know it's along the threshold
somewhere, right at the entrance
of the cave.
So logically, if that's true,
then it would be right
underneath here.
The problem is the clue
definitely says, "Dig deep."
That's the question, how deep do
I have to go?
And with a machete, it's not
easy to dig deep.
>> I took the whole camp out to
give Yau a chance to dig for
that immunity idol.
Hopefully, he goes with what I'm
trying to do.
Now, look at that.
That's what I'm talking about.
>> Earl and I decided we were
going to hike up, see if we
could find some more fruit or
anything edible.
And I tell you, we got up to the
hill, where you can see 360
degrees, all around the island.
We so rarely get a chance to
just take it in and just let
ourselves be astounded and awed
by what's around us.
It gives you new drive to keep
going.
In a battle of wills, which this
game is, you need every little
ounce of energy you can get to
keep you just emotionally going
forward.
>> The search for the immunity
idol is not going very well.
Trying to dig with that machete
is quite difficult-- to dig
deep, at least.
At this point, it's going to be
very difficult to get it.
>> Tree mail.
>> Time to go get our reward,
establish our new victory
streak.
>> Oh, pictures.
>> "Pick two choices for your
reward.
You win, you'll take it all.
If you lose, you'll just take a
beating."
Toiletries-- I saw toiletries!
>> Wine, cheese.
>> Oh, yeah, that one!
>> Oh!
>> I say we get the cake and the
toiletries.
>> The toiletries.
>> Are you going to change your
vote?
>> We keep getting more food,
more nourishment.
Ravu keeps getting less.
They're wasting away.
But we have the luxury of them
being down and malnourished and
us being fat and happy.
Who cares how much luxury?
We have so much luxury, it
doesn't matter.
>> I want the chocolate cake.
Can we please pick one thing
that we need and one thing we
want?
>> Yeah, one thing that we need
and something we can eat.
>> Two things we need, that'd be
the best thing, two things that
we need.
>> I'm starving.
>> Okay, we definitely want...
that's why we want fishing gear,
to catch fish.
We're not on Fantasy Island.
I don't want wine and cheese.
That doesn't do anything for me.
Moto is living in a mansion over
there, you know, The Fresh
Prince of Bel Air over there.
And we're like, you know, Good
Times.
You know, we're going to be
practical.
They should have put a couple of
Philly cheese steaks on there.
>> Don't start with the food
game!
>> PROBST: Ravu, come on in!
Moto, come on in!
Boo, can't help but notice that
you're coming in here chewing
on... what was that, mango?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Rocky, it's got to
burn a little bit.
>> I mean, look at my eyes.
There's fire coming out right
now.
Laugh it up.
It's all right.
We'll see what happens.
>> PROBST: Shall we get to
today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will square off
one on one on a platform.
Using large, padded bags, you
will battle sumo-style.
Your goal: knock the other tribe
member off the platform, into
the mud.
Winner scores a point for their
tribe.
First tribe to seven wins
reward.
The winning tribe will send one
member from the losing tribe to
Exile Island.
Let's get to the reward.
Ravu, you chose necessity, the
same fishing gear that Moto has
two sets of and a pot full of
potatoes, absolute essentials if
you guys are going to have any
shot in this game.
Life is so good for Moto, they
chose more luxury: coffee and
some toiletries.
Winner takes it all.
>> Keep it up, Dreamz.
Keep it up, guy, seriously.
Why don't me and you go up there
right now?
>> We could.
>> Let's do that then.
Keep running your mouth.
Bring it.
Bring it, bro.
I'm sick of this guy.
Let's go, Jeff.
Let's play the game.
>> PROBST: Do we have our first
match?
Is it Rocky and Dreamz?
>> That's what it is.
>> PROBST: All right.
There's one rule.
Each person has to go at least
once.
>> You got to show us what
you're made of, man.
>> PROBST: Ravu looking for
their first win.
Moto wants to remain undefeated.
Survivors ready?
>> Let's go, man.
>> All right, Rock.
>> PROBST: Go.
>> Get angry, you'll win, Rocky.
Come on.
>> Come on, Dreamz.
>> Come on, Rocky.
>> Go, Dreamz, go!
Go, Dreamz, go!
( cheering )
>> Yeah, yeah!
>> PROBST: Moto scores first
point.
Moto leads 1-0.
( cheering )
It is Cassandra versus Rita.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Go, Cassandra!
>> PROBST: Cassandra uses her
body, knocks Rita in.
Moto leads two-zip.
Next round, Edgardo taking on
Anthony.
Anthony looks like he's got a
little fire in his belly.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Come on, Ed!
>> PROBST: Anthony is in.
Moto leads three-zip.
Next round, it is Lisi taking on
Michelle.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Lisi hits her hard, pushes her
off with no trouble.
Moto leads four-zip.
It's first tribe to seven.
Boo taking on Earl.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Come on, Boo!
>> Let's go, Earl!
>> Go, Boo, go!
>> Come on, Boo!
>> Come on, Boo, get him!
>> PROBST: Boo pushes Earl off.
Moto leads five-zip.
It is Alex taking on Mookie.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, Alex!
Go, Alex!
Go!
>> Come on, Alex!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Moto leads six-zip.
We're down to the last two tribe
members in this round.
We have Yau-Man now squaring off
against Stacy.
>> Bulldoze him!
>> PROBST: Moto leads six-zip.
Stacy wins here, it's over.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Go, Stacy, go!
Go, Stacy, go!
>> Push, Stacy, push!
>> Come on, Stacy!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Stacy in the water!
Ravu scores their first point.
>> That a boy, Yau.
>> Yeah, Yau.
>> Do what you got to do.
>> PROBST: Here's where we
stand: Moto leads 6-1.
This is a grudge match,
Cassandra taking on Rita once
again.
Cassandra could win it for Moto
right here.
Survivors ready?
Go.
A hard push and a big fall for
Rita.
Moto wins reward!
Moto, you will now send one
person from the Ravu tribe to
Exile Island.
Who's it going to be?
>> Earl.
>> PROBST: Earl, you will return
in time for the next immunity
challenge.
Straight out this way, Earl.
Ravu, once again I got nothing
for you.
Moto, congratulations on another
win.
Fishing gear, potatoes,
toiletries, coffee, it's all
yours.
Head on back.
>> Oh, my god!
I love coffee.
>> This is clean.
I have not smelled anything
clean in a long, long time.
>> Let's make coffee.
Let's make coffee.
Let's make coffee now.
>> Oh!
That challenge was a winner-
take-all situation.
Either we were going to get
coffee, toiletries, bag of
potatoes, and yet again the
fishing gear, or we were going
to lose it all and potentially
lose our advantage.
So it was a big deal.
>> Coffee.
Aw, they even gave us floss.
That's all right.
Y'all ain't got to talk to me.
It's cool.
>> Dreamz and Cassandra have no
allies on this team.
It's 5-2.
They're going to get picked off.
They know it.
They're getting paranoid.
It's not my problem.
We're all adults here.
There's no children.
I mean, come on.
It's Survivor.
>> This ain't the instant
dissolve coffee.
It's one you got to filter.
But it's so good.
( spitting )
>> What's going on, Boo... I
mean Dreamz?
You put the boiling water in
there with the coffee.
Yeah, you don't....
>> Do you know how to make it,
man?
>> Well, if you guys know how to
make it, tell him how to make
it.
>> That's cool.
Y'all can say that to my face,
you know, whatever y'all are
saying back there.
>> Stacy and Lisi I think, in
particular, are just downright
rude.
It kind of nauseates me to see
people being treated that way.
It really kind of just rubbed me
the wrong way.
Well, I don't know how to
freaking use it, so if someone
can tell me...
>> You have to boil water.
You put the coffee in the
bottom, you pour the boiling
water on top, and you let it sit
for about three minute, and then
you press it down, and then you
have coffee, simple as that.
>> This game to me is about
almost immediate karma, and why
they would treat other human
beings that way just as human
beings, and in the course of the
game, why they wouldn't see how
that might screw them in the
future.
>> Oh, my God, this is like a
little piece of heaven.
>> I'm really upset at Stacy and
Lisi, because they're on a power
trip, and if they're in my
alliance and they keep going
that way, I'm going to make sure
they're out.
>> This is, like, the best day
so far.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yau's been to Exile Island,
so him and I have an
understanding.
I gave him this opportunity to
actually look for the idol when
I took everybody on the
excursion, and he says he
couldn't find it.
>> Clue number five: "Under the
entrance, under the ground,
right where you're living, the
idol is found."
I know that already.
I trust Yau.
It pretty much just came down to
not having the right tools.
I don't think he'll find it
before I get back, but you never
know.
>> Sorry I didn't have the sumo
technique down, but it's not my
forte, you know?
The only sumo I watched was...
was what's it called?
Austin Powers, Fat Bastard.
>> Isn't it funny that we're
both really into fashion?
>> I know.
And for me, truthfully, I go
out, I'm just lip gloss, good to
go.
Because if I have to... on top
of that, when I go and work,
have to put all that stuff on, I
don't want to put that on.
I mean, models walk around like
this all day.
I know for myself, my daily
makeup routine is lip gloss and
I'm out.
And of course we fare better
because we're... our ethnic skin
is really on our side.
>> The whole lip-gloss thing,
girl thing is really not my
thing.
Basically, I want to take my
T-shirt and hang myself from a
palm tree.
>> So he's like, "Rita, why
don't we go out tomorrow for
lunch?
Bring your friend."
>> My ears are oozing.
You see this?
That's the brain coming out.
>> Let me say it to you like
this.
If we all had, like, a one-
bedroom apart, there was four of
us in there, right?-- all right,
let's say me and you woke up
earlier than everybody else all
the time, and we had some things
we just had to talk about, you
go out of the room.
All these conversations they
have are absolutely stupid.
I want to smack them with a
fried pineapple.
I don't know what to do.
It's driving me absolutely
crazy.
>> I'm one of those people that
look high-maintenance, but I'm
so low maintenance.
>> So I've done the math on
this, right?
>> Uh-huh.
>> So let's assume we merge with
ten people.
>> Uh-huh.
>> If we win every single
immunity, we end up with us
seven, Ravu has three, Cassandra
and Dreamz switch over, now it's
five and five voting-wise.
>> Cool, whatever.
>> No, it's not cool, whatever.
We don't have the majority
anymore.
You know, for some reason, the
whole situation with Dreamz and
Cassandra had just... it had
really been... sort of been
eating away at me, and I started
to do a little bit of math.
Do you see the obvious, like,
issue we have here?
>> We do not need to do business
with them at all, seriously.
I don't think we should include
Dreamz and Cassandra on
anything.
>> Excluding Cassandra and
Dreamz is the dumbest thing we
could do.
If we don't keep them happy,
they're going to flip-flop.
Then we're all screwed.
>> Yeah, but we want them all
gone.
>> Yeah, see, dude, but...
Oh, God, kill me!
Kill me!
Kill me right now!
How do you not understand what
I'm trying to say to you?
>> I had a little talk with
Alex, and we're like, "Listen,
if Stacy and Lisi are going to
be like this, let's keep
Cassandra and Dreamz close."
>> Boo is so dumb too.
Boo does whatever they say.
>> They think because five,
they're in control.
They're not thinking further
ahead like you and me.
So we're kind of the peace
keepers in this tribe right now.
We're trying to put our chess
pieces in place so when we start
really playing the game, we have
them at the right place at the
right time.
>> Now, we're going to have our
internal whatevers, but at the
end of the day, we're a team,
and the goal is to take Ravu out
and make it as far as we can,
because we deserve every victory
we've earned.
>> I came back to the shelter,
and it was like they'd embraced
me again.
It was like a warm embrace
again.
It didn't change my strategy of
what to do come the merge.
When we get into the merge, me
and Cassandra are going to leave
and go with the other tribe.
>> Let's just continue to
battle, remember we're a team,
and just bang it out, just bang
it out.
>> Is that a solid solidarity,
guys?
>> It's a solid solidarity,
guys.
>> Solid?
>> Everybody?
>> That's a great plan,
genocide, genocide.
Saying genocide and wiping out
Ravu, that's just part of the
game now.
It's like poker.
You bluffing, acting like you
got something when you don't.
They're always talking about
"Hey, it's a game; it's just
strategy."
So I'm going to just show them.
I can't wait till the day to put
on my snakeskin boots to show
them strategy.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Earl
returning from Exile Island.
>> Hey, Earl!
>> What's going on?
( applause )
>> PROBST: Shall we get to
today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First thing's first.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, your
memory will be tested.
Scattered in the field are 30
boards.
Each board has a number or a
word painted on it.
One tribe member at a time will
reveal two boards.
If the numbers or words match,
you score a point for your
tribe.
First tribe to seven wins
immunity, guaranteed at least
one more day out here in Fiji.
Losers, tribal council tonight,
somebody going home.
To make it a little more
complicated, there are four
dummy boards that do not have a
match.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize.
We'll get started.
Moto won the rock, paper,
scissor.
Once you leave the platform,
there is no coaching from your
tribe.
Edgardo heads out for Moto.
Edgardo flips over the seven.
Trying to use his ESP and flips
over the priest-- no match.
Rocky heads out for Ravu.
Rocky reveals the nine.
Going somewhere new, hoping to
get lucky.
No luck.
Rocky reveals the four.
Cassandra heads out for Moto.
Cassandra would like to reveal
something that's already been
shown.
Cassandra reveals the eight, yet
another new number.
Cassandra hoping to get lucky.
Cassandra...
( cheering )
Cassandra lucks into a match.
Moto on the board with their
first pair.
Mookie would like the same kind
of luck, walk into a match.
Mookie flips over a ten.
Mookie flips over the seven,
which excites Moto.
Boo, he's jogging he's so
excited.
Boo flips over the first seven.
Does he remember where the
second seven is?
Boo flips it over and has the
second match for Moto.
Moto up two-zip.
Rita heads out for Ravu.
Rita flips over the 14.
Once again, Ravu will need some
luck.
A three.
No score for Ravu.
Stacy flips over a five.
And Stacy flips over the priest.
Ravu very excited.
Yau-Man heading out on the
course for Ravu.
Yau-Man reveals one priest.
Can he remember where the second
priest just was?
Yau-Man surveying the course,
trying to remember, hasn't eaten
much in a long time.
That sharp brain is a little
soft.
No help.
No need to look this way.
You're just going to tempt your
tribe into losing a turn.
Yau-Man cannot ask his tribe for
help.
It's all on him.
Yau-Man makes his selection, and
it is wrong.
Yau-Man chooses princess, does
not match up with priest.
Chance for Ravu to get in this
game just slipped through their
fingers.
Moto.
Ooh!
Lisi so excited she takes a face
plant.
Lisi runs right to the first
priest.
( tribe groans )
>> PROBST: No, no!
Lisi, back to the platform.
Just to be clear, Lisi, you lost
your turn because your tribe
spoke.
You cannot do that.
You lose a turn.
Ravu's turn.
>> Go, go.
>> You got it, you got it.
>> PROBST: Big opportunity for
Ravu.
Will Ravu take back the
opportunity that Yau-Man lost?
Earl lifts the first priest.
Earl, very confident, flips the
second priest.
Ravu on the board with their
first point.
Dreamz reveals the number five.
Dreamz trying to remember.
Where was the other five?
Dreamz reveals the number ten.
No match for Moto.
>> Right here, the right of
that.
>> Right?
>> Right.
>> PROBST: Anthony out on the
course for Ravu.
Anthony could tie it up.
Anthony reveals a five.
Looking to match up that five.
Is he right?
He is.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Anthony scores for
Ravu.
We are tied 2-2.
( applause )
>> PROBST: Alex matches up the
three.
Rocky on the board for Ravu.
>> What!
>> PROBST: We remain tied.
Edgardo matches the two.
( applause )
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Ravu scores again.
Stacy looking to match the ten,
and she does.
Yau-Man looking for that match.
Alex is looking to match up...
...tie this game back up.
Alex scores another match.
And we are tied 6-6.
All right, it comes down to
this.
There is only one matching pair
left in the field.
The rest are dummy boards.
So the tribe that matches that
last pair wins immunity.
Ravu, you're up.
Michelle could win it for Ravu
right here.
Michelle flips over the 13.
If she matches the 13, Ravu wins
their first challenge.
( groaning )
She does not.
Edgardo heads out for Moto.
He could win it for Moto.
Edgardo flips the 12.
If he flips the 12, Moto wins.
Edgardo flips the nine, does not
match.
Ravu again with an opportunity.
>> Tell me where to go.
>> Out between....
>> Come on, just give me
something.
>> Okay.
>> Shh, come on!
>> 13, 14...
>> PROBST: Rocky heading out for
Ravu.
Ravu could win it if Rocky can
match up two symbols.
He quickly flips the nine.
( Rocky laughs )
Only a few boards left to
reveal.
If Rocky matches the nine, Ravu
wins their first challenge.
Rocky flips over the 12, no
match for Ravu.
Ravu squanders a huge
opportunity and opens the door
for Moto to continue their
winning streak.
Cassandra reveals the nine.
Cassandra could win it right
here.
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Cassandra reveals the
nine.
Moto wins immunity, remains
undefeated.
>> Argh!
>> PROBST: Moto,
congratulations.
>> Thank you.
( applause )
>> PROBST: Immunity once again,
safe from tribal council.
Ravu, very close, just couldn't
pull it together when you needed
to.
We have a date tonight at
tribal.
Somebody from this tribe is
going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Yo, can I say something real
quick or no?
I'm going to take the majority
of the blame today, okay?
Because you know, it was up to
me at the end.
And between all the talk...
like, just I had a mental
breakdown.
You know, I didn't even know
what number we were going for,
to be honest with you.
So I dropped the ball.
I want to apologize for that.
But at the same time, this mass
confusion thing, everyone
talking at the same time,
everyone going ( gibbering )
like that, like, in our dire
straits right now, mentally, how
can anybody like...
>> Concentrate.
>> ...concentrate or comprehend
absolutely anything?
>> People have to listen and
know when to be quiet, like...
>> It's not like I'm yelling at
anybody.
It's just...
>> No, but, you know, everyone
has to really put the brakes on
and know when to step back and
be quiet, because...
>> Let me ask you a question.
When we were winning, when we
were this close, is that the
best you've felt since you've
been here?
That's the best I've felt in 14
days.
>> Getting rid of Rocky would
probably get rid of a lot of the
friction in the tribe.
If you lay your cards on the
like that at this point, when
people are looking for anything,
absolutely anything to get rid
of somebody, don't be surprised
if people follow up on it.
>> Rita is running her mouth all
day, guys.
All she does is run her mouth.
All through the challenge,
that's all she was doing.
>> "It's over here!
It's over here!
It's over here!"
A lot of us have been looking at
Rita.
Some folks are really sick of
hearing from Rita.
Around the last vote, my head
was on the chopping block, but
I'm going to keep my ears open
and hope nobody tries to flip
the script on me, because right
now this is still anybody's
vote.
>> Oh, my God.
>> What do you want to do
tonight?
>> Is Anthony okay with you
then?
>> That's fine.
>> Anthony okay with you?
>> Uh-huh.
>> All right.
Anthony okay with you, Yau-Man?
All right, it's done.
>> Yup, we got our majority
right there, so just let Rocky
know, okay?
>> Yeah, I'm coming.
>> That mouth of hers, it drives
me... am I wrong?
Am I wrong, all the yakking and
talking, bro?
>> Well, you know what's funny
is Anthony has been...
>> Shady, bro.
>> He's starting to gain, like,
a little confidence or
something.
Like personally, I'd like to
take him out, but...
>> I got to get rid of Rita
first, bro.
I mean, worst comes to worst, he
can be next, but Rita's got to
go, buddy.
Like, I don't know what's up
with your boy Anthony.
You know him better than me.
I don't know if he's being shady
or whatever.
So I need you my side.
>> Usually I'm the person that
brings up strategy, like, "Well,
let's do this, let's do that."
The other people are starting to
devise their own plans.
I think before they were just
going with the majority, but it
seems like everyone's doing
their own thing, trying to play
their own game now.
You have to watch your back.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, you were so
close.
How frustrating is it?
>> It's very frustrating, and
for me, personally, it was very
embarrassing.
My brains went into neutral when
it came to my turn, and I
couldn't remember something I
saw 30 seconds ago.
I hope it's a temporary
condition, because otherwise I'm
in bad shape.
>> PROBST: Mookie, did you guys
get beat today, or did you give
it away?
>> Jeff, it's hard to, you know,
follow through when everyone's
talking to you at one time.
I know Rocky came up and took
the blame for the last point,
and it wasn't completely his
fault.
We all jumped in, and we all
told him where we thought things
were, and you know, we confused
him.
>> PROBST: Rocky, why are you
trying to take the fall?
>> I swear if we would have won
that challenge, that whole
island would have exploded.
We were so close, and I took
that away from myself, and I
took that away from my tribe,
and I felt bad.
>> PROBST: Rita, you're going
through something very extreme.
When you get tired of thinking
how bad things are, what do you
talk about to get your mind off
of things?
>> Well, I tell little stories
that I think might be
interesting to keep their mind
off this dire situation that
we're in and try to keep
everybody entertained.
>> PROBST: Earl, are we at a
point in the game where the
reasons you vote somebody out
are starting to change?
>> I do believe the reasons are
starting to change.
I really think before, some of
the decisions were pretty quick.
But I think now people are
starting to get to know one
another.
I think it's about the
chemistry.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, been out
here long enough that you can
now say you trust the people in
this tribe anyway?
>> My credo in life is love
many, trust few, do wrong to
none.
So the question is what is few?
Whether I trust them depends on
whether my strategy dovetails
with theirs or not.
>> PROBST: Anthony, as we get
ready to go to the vote, how
uncomfortable are you that it
might be you?
>> Fairly uncomfortable.
I mean, my personality does
clash with some people, and they
may think that I'm trying
something when I'm trying to
bring as much honesty to people
as I can.
>> PROBST: Okay, if anybody has
the hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, you would
present it to me after the votes
have been cast but before I read
them.
It is time to vote.
Earl, you're up.
>> As you know, this tribe works
from majorities, and at this
point, I couldn't go against
them.
>> We had our differences, but I
like you a lot.
Good luck.
>> It comes down to who is the
most disposable.
Sorry, nothing personal.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now is the time to do
so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Anthony.
Rita.
One vote Rita.
Anthony.
Two votes Anthony.
Rita.
Two votes Anthony, two votes
That's three votes Rita, two
votes Anthony.
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji, Rita.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Rita, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Thank you.
Good luck.
>> PROBST: Well, the good news
is today's challenge showed you
still have the will to win.
That will is what you got to
hang on to tomorrow morning when
you get up to start another day.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
Drop your buffs.
>> What?
>> ...a major shake-up...
>> Come on, Dreamz.
>> PROBST: Maybe the biggest
rivalry thus far just paired up.
...changes everything.
>> Right now we're a super
power.
>> PROBST: One very big decision
left to make.
Which group is going to live on
the Moto beach and which group
is going to Ravu?
>> I'm really surprised, and I'm
sad at the result tonight, but I
understand it's a game.
I really tried to stay true and
honest, and I did trust my
alliances.
So maybe I was just too nice to
play the game.
But if that's the case, I leave
this game feeling very proud.
I just hope that I have made my
kids proud, because that's main
reason that I did this.