>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> That was brilliant.
>> PROBST: With the four
horsemen's alliance broken,
Alex and Mookie were on the
outs.
>> We are six strong, and
there's two people just waiting
on death row.
>> PROBST: In a desperate
attempt to save their necks,
Alex and Mookie searched
through Yau-Man's bag.
>> Yeah, he got it.
>> PROBST: And discovered his
hidden immunity idol.
>> Just cause some hell, man.
If I'm going down, I'm bringing
hell with me.
>> PROBST: When Alex and Mookie
confronted Yau-Man...
>> What do you want to do, Yau?
>> You guys do what you need to
do.
>> PROBST: ...he decided to
tell everyone about the idol.
>> I thought that was a little
dirty, but I will have to tell
all my voting bloc straight out.
They went through my bag.
>> They went through your bag,
Yau-Man?
>> Yeah, they went through my
bag.
>> Alex went through Yau-Man's
things and threatened him.
They said, "I know you have the
immunity idol."
>> Finding out that Yau-Man had
the immunity idol changed a
whole bunch of stuff because
everybody with the immunity
idol is considered dangerous.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
Mookie connects!
...The tribe was split into two
teams.
Dreamz has it!
Green wins reward!
Dreamz secured victory for
himself, Stacy, Earl and Alex.
Boo, head on out.
And they sent Boo to Exile
Island...
>> "The idol is back at your
very own beach."
>> PROBST: ...Where he
discovered the first clue to a
newly hidden immunity idol.
>> It's not here.
It's not my beach.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
>> D-4.
>> PROBST: D-4 is a hit.
Alex out.
Stacy wins individual immunity.
...Stacy came out on top.
Stacy, safe from tonight's
Tribal Council.
You are not.
There's somebody going home.
Back at camp:
Fearing that Alex or Mookie
could easily stumble upon the
newly hidden immunity idol, Boo
convinced his alliance to split
their vote.
Earl and Yau-Man, however, were
uneasy with the plan.
>> Going into tonight's Tribal
Council split vote worries me
very much.
I really... rather not see it.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council...
You cannot vote for Stacy.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Alex, you're up.
...in a last-ditch effort to
save himself, Alex turned on
Mookie and helped vote him out.
The 11th person voted out and
the fifth member of our jury:
Mookie.
Mookie, the tribe has spoken.
Well, based on what I heard
tonight, Alex is either odd man
out or suddenly very valuable.
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Tonight's vote was pretty
important for me.
I know Mookie voted for Boo.
I voted for Mookie.
>> My vote for Mookie is what
saved my ass, basically.
I was like, I'm gonna write
down his name, go with my gut.
So I'm still here.
(laughs)
Yup, still here.
>> I would have preferred Alex
would go.
Alex is more of a threat, but
for some strange reason, they
wanted to split the vote
between Mookie and Alex, and no
one considered the fact that,
hey, did you ever think that
Mookie and Alex have a vote?
That they might vote for each
other? Duh.
>> I don't want there to be,
like, some kinda rift between
you and I.
I'm willing to say if I'm wrong,
I'm wrong.
>> Whatever. You know.
It's not that big a deal.
After Tribal Council, Stacy
approached me, you know, trying
to clear things up, telling me
how she wants to be friends with
me after this. Like I care.
>> So I understand...
>> Who's "everybody?"
>> Everybody besides you and
Alex.
>> At this point, they're all
stressing out.
Obviously, they're not all in
agreement.
That always creates room and
opportunity.
>> Why am I... Why are y...
What's going on?
>> We're asking you a question.
>> I don't know.
>> No, because Boo came over and
he's like, "Everybody wants to
talk to you."
>> He just wants to know.
>> My best bet was to just lay
low, observe, let them get at
each other a little bit.
From this point forward, I
think I'm gonna have to play
this game with a smile, you
know, velvet gloves and a
dagger in my pocket.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> I definitely feel like I'm
on the chopping block still.
So after last night, I decided
I'm going into ninja mode and
it started this morning, right?
I woke up.
I could have gone up, you know,
gone around, done my business as
I normally do, but instead I
just kinda laid there and just
kinda listened, tried to see,
okay, who's still here?
Who's still at the campfire?
Like, it's all about observation
for me, and I'm trying to make
sure I'm not seen or heard,
kinda like a ninja right now.
>> Yau I trust 100%.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I only trust Yau and you
100%.
>> Oh, okay. Good.
>> Dreamz has been proving
himself.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> You know, he can be a little
rogue at times with his
strategy.
>> I'd look into that.
I always felt that I could rely
on Dreamz.
>> The core alliance is myself,
Cassandra and Yau, but me and
Cassandra talked about taking
Dreamz to the top four.
Then we can just have the, the
core four.
That's what they're called,
the core four.
>> I mean, honestly, my concern
is you and Dreamz are tight.
I mean, I don't see you voting
him out...
So I'm, just saying,
mathematically, I'm off to my
thing, you know.
Earl and I have a major
disagreement as to who the top
four should be.
His idea of the top four is
myself, Earl, Cassandra and
Dreamz.
That is a very bad top four for
me to get to the next stage
because Cassandra and, and
Dreamz are very close.
I would like a very weak
candidate up there, but the
very weakest is Stacy, I know.
I hate the idea; I really do.
I wish it was Michelle.
I would like to see the top
four as myself, Earl, Cassandra
and Stacy because then I have
a chance of getting to the top
three.
>> I trust Yau-Man, but Yau-Man
is definitely playing the game
for himself.
Yau has immunity idol, and so
I think Yau-Man is a real big
threat.
I know he's playing the game
and he's playing the game hard.
He's playing it like street
ball: he's playing it to win it.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How's everybody doing on day 31?
>> We all are tired out here.
>> Hungry.
>> PROBST: Hungry?
Hungry plays in nicely to
today's challenge.
Shall we get to it?
>> Yes.
>> Do it!
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you are going to rip
pieces of meat off a large
piece of pork using only your
teeth.
Each time you get a mouthful,
you'll drop it in your
plate.
Whoever has the most meat on
their plate at the end of five
minutes wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Tomorrow the winner
and the first two runners-up
will be picked up by helicopter,
flown to one of the most
beautiful places in Fiji.
Then you will river-raft the
rain forest.
>> Oh... wow!
>> PROBST: It is truly
spectacular.
You'll then have a nice lunch,
come back to camp.
In addition, the winner of this
challenge will send one person
to Exile Island.
Finally, the winner of this
challenge will also receive an
advantage in the next immunity
challenge.
Take your spot.
We'll get your hands tied
behind your back and we'll get
started.
Here we go.
For reward and an advantage in
the next immunity challenge.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You got five minutes to tear
off as much pork as you can and
get it on your plate.
There are no lanes.
This is a free-for-all.
Dreamz and Earl getting a good,
quick start.
Alex with a nice big piece.
Yau-Man, Boo, Cassandra working
together.
Nobody working with Alex.
Boo with a huge piece.
Yau-Man with a nice big chunk.
>> Cassandra.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man looking for
some help from Cassandra.
You need two people.
One to hold it steady.
One to tear it off.
Dreamz with another big piece.
Alex in it.
Cassandra still in it.
Alex staying in it.
Yau-Man with a huge chunk!
Earl picking it up off the dirt.
Yau-Man and Boo working
together using their shoulder,
using their chins.
Yau-Man with another huge chunk
of pork.
Boo gets a big chunk.
Boo is in it.
Cassandra is in it.
Yau-Man is in it.
Alex with another big piece.
It's going to be very close.
One and a half minutes left in
this challenge.
Dreamz is in it.
Alex not giving up.
15 seconds.
Whatever is in your mouth when
I call time also counts.
Five, four, three, two, one,
stop!
That's it!
Whatever you have in your
mouth, put on your plate.
Start with Boo.
Boo weighs in at 8.9 pounds.
Boo, take a spot right up here.
For now, you are in first place.
Yau-Man weighs in at six pounds.
Yau-Man, currently in second
place.
Cassandra comes in at 5.8
pounds.
Take a spot up here, Cassandra.
Stacy in at 4.3 pounds.
You can stay there.
Earl, not enough.
Five pounds.
Dreamz at six pounds also.
Dreamz, you replace Cassandra.
One plate left.
If this is under six pounds,
you're out of the reward, Alex.
It is not going to be enough.
Boo wins the challenge.
>> Finally!
>> PROBST: Yau-Man and Dreamz,
first runners-up.
You're going along with him on
the reward.
All right, Boo, first order of
business.
Since you won the challenge,
you earn the right to send one
person to Exile Island.
>> Earl, I know you don't take
hard feelings to this.
I'm going to send you back.
>> PROBST: Head on out.
Boat will pick you up.
You'll be back in time for the
next immunity challenge.
Boo, this is your advantage for
the next immunity challenge.
You can ponder how that might
come into play.
It will all make sense at the
next challenge.
All right, guys, head back to
camp.
>> Here it comes.
>> That's the one right there.
Get a helicopter ride!
All right, ladies and
gentlemen, keep the camp safe.
We'll do what we can do.
>> You guys have fun.
>> I won the reward challenge
yesterday, along with Boo and
Dreamz, and we start out the
day with a helicopter ride.
I've never been on a helicopter.
Very excited.
>> Fly like the birds.
>> I know. Right?
>> Wow!
This is so cool!
>> For real.
>> I'll be back!
>> Being in a helicopter flying
was truly amazing flight for
somebody like me who grew up on
islands like this, and to see it
from the air was just an amazing
experience.
>> Now we're going through the
rain forest.
>> Wow!
We're living la vida large!
>> How much you think it cost to
rent one of these?
I wouldn't mind spending, like,
$600 or $700 on a really nice
date.
I'd do it big like that, Dreamz.
>> There's Exile Island right
there.
>> What's up, Earl?
What's up, Earl?
Holy moley!
I still can't believe it.
We rolling up in here, folks!
Oh, this is comfortable.
>> During the reward, Boo was
talking a lot, just trying to
be... I don't know.
He was just talking too much.
>> Hello.
Can you hear me, Dreamz?
Hello.
>> It's relaxing time, you know?
It's time to chill.
We won this.
Let's relax.
Let's live it up.
It's just annoying.
>> I'm hungry.
We're going whitewater rafting,
the most beautiful place in
Fiji.
>> Oh, wow!
What a ride!
It was just unbelievable.
And about an hour and a half
into the trip, the helicopter
landed, and we had to hike for
about ten minutes to get to the
river.
>> So, personally, you guys, I
want to welcome you guys.
The name of this river is the
Apananuli.
Secondly, it's really fast and
so strong.
>> So we were given a little
safety briefing, and we got
into a raft with the river
guide, and then we went down
this rapids.
>> Then we went whitewater
rafting.
Probably never do it again, but
it was so fun.
And I wish I could take my
family or somebody on a trip
like that so they can
experience what I experienced.
>> Look at that!
Waterfall.
Now, that's a waterfall.
>> It's like a field trip for
grown people.
>> We're floating around in a
postcard here.
You cannot get better than this.
I told myself ten times, "Look
at this.
Take it in.
Look where you're at."
I am absolutely dumbfounded.
I mean, I'm tickled pink.
I feel like a little girl.
>> This is great.
>> This is what I came here for.
"Clue number two: Your normal
winding paths you'll walk.
It's inside a tree near a
lonely tower of rock."
I'll figure it out.
I think two clues will be
enough for me.
Can't wait to get back to camp
to go looking for that idol.
It would be all worth it.
>> Oh, is that caviar?
Oh, this is good beef.
>> That is awesome!
>> Look at that!
>> That's impressive, Dreamz.
>> We finally got to lunch, it
was just so much stuff.
And I just kept eating it.
We were back at camp living
like cavemen in the dirt,
having nothing, and living like
a broke, homeless guy, to living
like you're rich.
>> The best, best part is, at
the end of the lunch, our river
guide came over and gave each
of us an envelope.
And in the envelope are
letters from home.
>> "Dear Daddy, Miss you so
much.
I got six "A"s and one "B" in
algebra on my report card."
Why can't you get a "B" in
Spanish or something? Man!
Yeah!
>> I'm going to read mine.
"Hey, Boo, your dad and sister
are doing really well.
Your dad's horses are eating
well.
Dad's kids are eating well
also."
Everybody is eating well.
See, my family thinks...
Thanks, Mom.
Oh, what a bonus, huh?
Am I crying yet?
How you doing, Dreamz?
You all right?
>> When I read my sister's
letter, you know, she said a
lot of deep stuff.
She was saying that she never
thought that one of us would
have a chance, a opportunity.
She thought it was over for the
family.
You know, she thought that our
opportunity was up until, you
know, I had the opportunity to
come here, and it really touched
me that it was me that had the
opportunity to come, you know?
>> Dreamz!
>> It lets me know that she
still believes in me even if I
don't believe in myself, so it
really brought a lot out of me.
It lets me know that my fight
is just beginning.
I know what I got to do now.
I remember my purpose here.
>> This is the best reward yet,
you guys.
>> It's the best yet.
>> Awesome!
>> My mom said, "I know you can
make a good situation out of
anything.
You can't get tired of people."
>> But, with Boo, you get tired
of him.
He talks more than the girls
talk.
>> I'm not really tired of him.
It's just the talking.
>> During the helicopter ride,
Boo just almost spoiled the
trip for us.
He definitely just talks too
much.
Why don't you stop saying
stupid stuff?
>> He's been like that since
day one.
>> I cannot handle any more.
I'm not going to lie to you
people.
I cannot handle any more.
I'm losing it.
Boo has been irritating enough
to where I don't think these
people want Boo to get the
$1 million.
So, if somebody starts Boo
bashing, I'm going to feed the
fire.
I cannot deal anymore.
Sorry, guys.
If I hear something stupid, I
may call it out, and it may
cause friction.
People are not going to want to
see certain people win and,
right now, I don't see Boo
winning a popularity contest,
so if I can help steer things
in an anti-Boo campaign, I am
all for it.
>> I never liked Boo, and I
want Boo gone before Alex.
Alex is still fighting strong,
so I'm still making plans with
Alex.
So, point-blank, I'm just not
going to let Boo win.
>> I'm going to try my
damnedest, you know that.
You do the same.
If Boo wins immunity today, I
think I'm pretty much screwed.
Boo has a full belly and an
advantage in the next immunity
challenge.
But I need to keep myself alive
in this thing, so I am focusing
all of my energy, all of my
willpower on the challenge.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Earl,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Bula.
>> Bula Bula.
>> Great to see you.
>> Welcome back, Earl.
>> PROBST: Are you guys ready
to get to today's challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Stacy, take back immunity.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
All right, at the last reward
challenge, Boo, you won an
advantage in today's immunity
challenge.
Did you bring it with you?
>> Yes, I did.
>> PROBST: Those are climbing
steps, and they are a big part
of today's challenge.
Boo, because you already have
your steps, you do not have to
participate in the first round
of this challenge.
You move on to the final.
For the rest of you, on my
"go," you will race to dig up
your three climbing steps that
are buried in the sand.
When you have all three, you
race to the finish.
The first two people to get
their climbing steps join Boo
in the final.
For the final round, you will
use those climbing steps to help
you get to the top of a 12-foot
pole.
First person to get to the top,
grab their flag, wins immunity,
stays alive in this game.
For the rest of you, after 33
days, somebody will be going
home tonight at Tribal Council.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for spots,
we'll get started.
All right, here we go.
First two people to finish join
Boo in the final round.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
You're looking for three paddle
steps buried in different
places in everybody's lane.
Alex going after it, on a tear.
Cassandra barely making a dent
in that sand.
Yau-Man making his way down the
course.
Is he deep enough?
Dreamz has his first paddle
step!
Alex tearing up a lot of sand,
no luck.
Coming back to a new spot.
Cassandra, digging like a small
rabbit, as if it's going to be
buried one to two inches.
Yau-Man trying a very
interesting method-- hugging
that sand.
Dreamz has his second climbing
step.
Stacy digging but finding
nothing.
Alex has a huge hole.
Still no climbing step.
Pick up the pace!
You can rest later!
Or you can rest tomorrow, just
not at the beach.
Dreamz has his third climbing
step.
Dreamz moving on to the final
round with Boo.
One more person moving on.
Yau-Man has his first climbing
step.
Now Yau-Man knows how deep they
are.
Alex has his first climbing
step.
You're looking for three total.
Alex getting all of the sand
out of his lane and moving most
of it out onto Yau-Man's
course.
Yau-Man putting his sand back
in Alex's lane.
Alex has his second climbing
step.
Alex now with two climbing
steps.
Yau-Man has one.
Cassandra just waiting for it
to be over.
Alex has his third climbing
step.
And with that, Alex moves on to
the final round with Boo and
Dreamz.
For the final round, we have
Boo, Alex, and Dreamz.
First person to stand on top of
the post and grab their flag
wins immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Boo up quickly.
Alex right behind.
Boo skipping several cleats.
Alex scaling to the top!
Can he pull it off?
Boo is up there!
Boo wins immunity!
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
(cheering)
>> PROBST: That's three people
who desperately wanted immunity.
That is not the easy way to do
this challenge.
Boo not even waiting for an
invitation.
>> Give it to me, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Boo safe from the
vote tonight.
Yau-Man, Earl, Stacy,
Cassandra, Dreamz, and Alex,
somebody going home tonight.
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> Fortunately for us, the
person who we wanted to vote out
today did not win the immunity
necklace, so... Alex will get
voted out today.
>> Can we sit here and say,
well, everybody right now,
Alex's name, please?
>> No, I'm going to give him
this necklace.
>> I'll freakin' tackle you.
That would be the greatest
Tribal Council ever 'cause we'd
be fighting all in there.
>> Today I'm feeling quite safe
because we have all agreed that
Alex is the odd man out and
needs to be taken out, so I'm
feeling safe enough that I do
not think I will need to use my
hidden immunity idol.
>> The situation is grim.
But, you know, I'm not going to
approach these people with
desperation.
I'm not going to beg for my
life.
That's not the way it works for
me.
Right now, taking an aggressive
approach to anything would be a
bad idea, especially given my
position.
I think the people that I need
to talk to will talk to me.
I think they'll approach me.
I think I've earned enough of
their respect they'll all at
least want to say something to
me before tonight's vote.
>> Hey, Alex.
>> Hey, Cassandra.
>> I hate to see you back down
here by yourself.
>> I'm okay.
I'm just tired.
>> You're just tired?
I know we started out
together...
>> Yeah, we did.
>> Just relax.
You should be very proud of
yourself.
We all are.
>> Yeah, I tried to be a
gentleman, you know.
I tried to give it my all and
do something that my kids could
be proud of someday.
>> Oh, okay.
Mm-hmm.
That's true.
Alex is trying his last effort
to make a pitch to stay on
longer, and he presented a
strong case.
His argument was that Yau-Man
has the idol, and he's going to
take Boo and Stacy with him
because he knows, their
personalities, people are not
going to vote for them to get
the million dollars.
It all started to make a little
sense.
I felt like, you know, Yau-Man
is going to eventually have to
leave, so why not tonight?
Maybe I'll be able to convince
other people of that.
>> I get nervous when I'm
alone, you know.
They're all talking about me.
>> I don't think so.
>> I anticipated this.
So Alex is just trying to save
his neck and say, "You guys
should use my vote.
This is your only chance to
take Yau-Man out."
But you know what?
I'd rather just vote your ass
off now, and I'll risk it.
>> Alex was talking to Cassandra
and Dreamz, and they seemed
like they were listening, but
they weren't.
I kind of like winked at them a
couple of times.
You know, you just play along
with him.
I don't think they're taking it
serious.
>> You really buying this?
>> I'm buying it, but I'm
like, then where does Alex fit
in everywhere?
>> He don't.
That's the whole thing, he's
gonna... after me, you and Earl,
the whole plan, regardless of
what happens, it's me, you and
Earl getting to the top three.
>> You know, Dreamz, like I told
you from day one...
>> I really want to do that
tonight.
The plan was to get rid of Alex
tonight, but Alex is my friend,
and Yau-Man has the immunity
idol, and that makes him so
dangerous.
Yau-Man has already said that I
was a big threat, so if he could
put that immunity idol into
play, that means he goes to try
to get rid of me.
>> You're down with that?
>> Yup.
>> Cassandra, what do you want
to do?
>> I'm down with you, Dreamz.
I told you from day one...
>> And I'm like a freakin'
follower.
I follow Cassandra.
>> If Cassandra's down with
this, it's gonna definitely go
through.
>> It's pretty safe to say if I
vote Yau-Man out, Stacy and
Dreamz will more than likely
vote with me.
And so, um, I definitely have a
choice to make, either to vote
Alex or Yau-Man.
And at this point right now,
I'm very undecided.
I'm not sure what I'm going to
do tonight.
>> I'm writing down A-L-E-X.
>> Mm-hmm.
I think Earl is very close
to Yau-Man.
There's no way he'd go for it.
So in order to blindside
Yau-Man, we definitely feel like
we have to blindside Earl at the
same time.
And so um, my head is telling me
one thing, and my heart is
saying another thing.
So I'm hoping that by the time
it's time for Tribal Council,
I'll have a clear feeling
exactly who I'm going to vote
for.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the jury.
Rocky, Lisi, Michelle, Edgardo,
and Mookie, voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
Alex, last Tribal Council, it
was you or Mookie.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: Mookie's over there.
>> I'm definitely feeling the
heat, Jeff.
But I told these guys, if I'm
going to be in this, you know
me, I'm going to fight to the
very end.
And for people who are sitting
here you have to consider who
you really want next to you.
And, you know, people forget
alliances.
Things are going to get very,
very messy from this point
forward whether I'm here or not.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, if something
dramatic was going to happen,
tonight's a good name night for
it.
You got six people.
Suddenly Alex becomes very
valuable.
Does that concern you?
>> I've thought about that
scenario, but because I have
been with my alliance for so
long, I have decided that I can
actually trust them up to this
point.
I can see maybe turning one,
possibly two, but to be able to
turn three over, that's a very
remote possibility at this time.
I may be wrong, but I hope I'm
not.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, do you
believe that these six are as
tight as they say?
It's Alex tonight, that's it,
and then tomorrow we deal with
the six?
>> It's definitely a
possibility that he can swing
three people, you know what I
mean.
It's not totally out of the
question.
>> PROBST: Alex, you obviously
had to try to do something
today.
Do you lie down and die or do
you start looking for cracks?
>> I guess we'll find out
tonight, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about the
hidden immunity idol.
Yau-Man, in some ways it
represents safety.
In other ways, you could be a
target simply because you have
it.
>> I don't feel the pressure
today, but the next round, I
think I will feel the pressure
when the six original alliance
members are going to look
around for somebody to vote
out, they may decide to flush
the idol out so that I cannot
use it for some nefarious
purpose, so at that point I
will have to really keep
my ears close to the ground and
see what's going on.
>> PROBST: Alex, what kind of
chatter has there been about
the other hidden immunity idol?
>> With one immunity idol out
and another one possibly on its
way, I mean, that's got to weigh
in on people's minds.
You can only use them tonight,
the next Tribal Council and
the one after that.
That's three opportunities, two
idols.
You do the math on that.
If it doesn't go down tonight,
it's going down in the next
couple of Tribal Councils.
So now or never.
Maybe the next time might be now
or never.
You just never know.
>> PROBST: Are you surprised
how unconcerned these six seem
to be?
>> I'm very surprised by it.
I mean either they are
completely 100% trustworthy or
they haven't seen enough of this
game.
I mean, if it really comes down
to them six after this, they
have to think people are
thinking more than one
move ahead.
It's very plausible.
There are only a few days left.
You got to think ahead, I think,
at this point.
>> PROBST: Before we get to the
vote, one quick question: yes
or no answer, Alex, legitimately
concerned tonight?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Cassandra?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Dreamz?
>> I don't think so, Jeff, not
now.
>> PROBST: Stacy, legitimately
concerned?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man?
>> PROBST: Earl?
>> No.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
If somebody does have a hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, you would present it to
me before I read the votes.
Boo, you have individual
immunity.
Are you going to hang on to
that?
>> Yes, I will, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Cannot vote for Boo.
Everybody else is fair game.
Alex, you're up.
>> Nothing personal, Yau-Man.
Just trying to stay in this as
long as I can.
>> Good-bye.
It's finally time for you to go.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has a hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now is the time to do
so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Alex.
Yau-Man.
One vote Yau-Man.
Alex.
Two votes Alex,
one vote Yau-Man.
Alex.
That's three votes Alex,
one vote Yau-Man.
12th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury: Alex.
You need to bring me your torch.
Alex, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, based on what I heard
tonight, I'd suggest you head
back to camp, start sharpening
those knives.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Yau-Man's in trouble.
And the competition reaches a
whole new level.
>> PROBST: you're willing to
take that risk?
>> Yes.
>> I know that I played this
game to the best of my ability.
I gave it 110% every single day
I was out here.
For all the kids who feel like
their situation is hopeless,
just remember to never stop
dreaming, never stop fighting.
You can and will amaze yourself.
I think the six remaining
members are living in a dream
world if they think that they're
not going to have to backstab
each other.
I mean things are going to get
very ugly at this point.