>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
The two tribes paddled to Exile
Island and merged into one.
>> "Drop your old buffs and wear
these new ones as you paddle to
your home, the old Moto camp."
>> I'll probably get a turn at
the bed tonight.
Finally, things are looking up.
>> PROBST: When they returned to
Moto's beach of luxury...
>> What the hell?
>> PROBST: ...everything was
gone.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Oh, no.
This is like a bad dream.
>> No bed, no couch, no shelter,
no nothing.
>> PROBST: The new merged tribe
contained two alliances-- the
Four Horsemen of Alex, Edgardo,
Mookie, and the not-so-reliable
Dreamz...
>> Unless I'm mistaken, the four
of us are controlling this game
right now.
>> PROBST: ...and a separate
alliance of four.
>> There's a tribe within the
tribe-- myself, Michelle,
Cassandra and Yau.
>> PROBST: Leaving Stacy and Boo
on the outs.
Mookie finally told Dreamz about
finding the hidden immunity idol
at the old Ravu camp.
>> But you can't say a word.
>> Do I look like... shut up!
We had a pact, and it kind of
made me not trust them a little
bit, and made me feel I'm on the
outskirts.
So I'm going to trust them until
I can't trust them no more.
>> PROBST: And the Four
Horsemen's alliance began to
fall apart.
>> They just want Stacy on their
side to take one of us out.
>> No way, no.
Point blank, no.
>> PROBST: In order to protect
themselves, Mookie and Dreamz
decided to go against the Four
Horsemen and target Stacy.
>> I'll really looking forward
to voting off Stacy.
She's got to go.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Reveal.
If you have orange go to the
orange mat.
If you have green, go to the
green mat.
A twist temporarily split the
tribe into two random teams.
Yau-Man working quickly.
The orange team is heading out.
And Yau Man proved himself a
valuable asset.
Yau-man makes a last-minute
switch, and it's a good thing he
did.
Orange team wins immunity and
reward!
Michelle, Stacy, Alex, Mookie,
Dreamz, you will not be going
back to camp.
We're heading to tribal council
right now.
At tribal council...
Ninth person voted out and the
third member of our jury...
Dreamz waffled and betrayed
Mookie when he voted for
Michelle instead of Stacy.
Michelle, the tribe has spoken.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Guaranteed, I think, Michelle
or Stacy are gone.
>> Who is Dreamz more tight
with?
>> I don't know, because he
doesn't like Stacy at all.
>> Welcome home.
>> Voting suck?
>> Yeah, it sucked.
>> I guess you could say I'm
pretty upset right now.
Earlier on, Dreamz and I had a
conversation of exactly going
back to the original plan that
we had, that we would take out
Stacy.
But Dreamz still votes off
Michelle.
We just basically gave all the
power to Alex.
You know, we just basically
screwed ourselves.
>> I made it very clear I that
was voting for Michelle.
I thought you were, like, doing
your own thing.
I was like...
>> No.
>> Okay, that's fine.
It's just miscommunication.
But listen, the way to seal the
final four in blood is to take
the immunity idol and rotate it.
Each of us gets it a day, and
that way...
>> That does nothing.
>> It does, dude.
It does.
>> It doesn't do anything.
>> It does.
It does, Mookie.
Because what it tells me and
tells everybody is that none of
us can screw each other over.
If I... look, the three of us
found it together.
You started digging in one area,
I pointed to another area.
We were all digging.
You happened to be the first one
to touch it.
And now you're telling me you're
not going to part with it unless
only on your terms.
That's messed up, dude.
>> I'm not saying that.
>> That's exactly what you're
saying.
You're saying something
different?
Be honest, man.
>> You know what?
What's going to happen now is
Alex is like, "You know what?
You have to trust us, and we're
each going to share the immunity
idol.
We're going to hold it once
every day."
Then he's like, "Four Horsemen
is nothing."
No we can't.
No we don't, because they don't
trust us.
This is what just... you screwed
everything with that.
>> When we got to tribal
council, Michelle start talking.
And when she says in the tribal
council, "I don't know Dre,
I never hung around him,"
it kind of let me know, "Wait a
minute, I don't know her
neither.
I don't know what alliance she's
in."
So it kind of scared me a little
bit, so it caused me to vote her
name.
If she never said that, she'd
still be here right now.
>> You did, trust me.
Don't worry about it.
Trust me.
You just screwed both of us.
>> Well, the tribe, the other
half returned from tribal
council, and I was hoping that
Stacy was gone.
It was definitely a shock.
I was very disappointed, and
that just flipped the whole
script around for everything in
my head.
>> If you all want to take me in
as a swing vote we'll make it to
the five with me, you,
Cassandra, Yau-- because I know
you're tight with Yau, Yau's a
solid, solid, person-- and
Dreamz.
The rest of them, they're all
backstabbers.
>> I think ... I mean, as long
as we take out Alex first.
>> That's fine with me, but the
thing is Dreamz is not going to
want to take Alex out.
>> You think Dreamz is not going
to want to take Alex out?
>> He likes Alex.
>> When Boo and I had our man-
to-man talk and looked each
other in the eye and
said he was with me, I still
didn't buy it.
Boo is just trying to save his
own neck at all times.
But I need to know if he's with
us.
I mean, because we really need
his vote since we don't have
Michelle.
That should go a few hours.
Basically, the main core is
myself, Yau, and Cassandra.
I trust them completely.
Dreamz is definitely a wild card
and I don't know if I trust
Mookie all the way yet, because
he's already kind of... tries to
manipulate a lot as well.
It's that part of the chess game
where you've already lost a
couple of really good pieces,
and now you have to really
think.
You can't trust everybody.
But I like playing this game.
And I am still here.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, we're going to test
how in tune are you with the
rest of your tribe.
I have a series of questions.
Each of you are going to answer
these questions in private.
I'll tally the results, then
I'll explain the challenge.
Let's go.
Okay, I have tallied the
results.
Now I'm going ask you these same
questions again, only this time
you're trying to guess what the
group said-- in other words,
whose name came up the most
often.
That may differ from what you
wrote down.
You're looking to match the
group consensus.
Each time you get it right, you
get to smash another tribe
member's tower.
When your three towers are gone,
you're out of the challenge.
The last person left standing
wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
The winner of this challenge
will spend the night on a
70-foot luxury yacht.
>> Whoo!
All right!
>> PROBST: You'll have a snack
and cocktail when you get on
board, a nice barbecue.
You'll spend the night on the
yacht in a comfortable bed.
In addition, the winner of this
challenge will send one person
to Exile Island.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: We'll get started.
All right, so remember, you're
looking to match the consensus
as a group whose name came up
the most often.
First question-- who would you
trust with your life?
Reveal.
The answer most commonly given
by the group was Earl.
Yau-Man got it right.
Cassandra got it right.
And Boo got it right.
Cassandra drew the strike first.
You're up.
>> Just random, anybody?
>> PROBST: It's not random.
Your reason, your choice.
You're giving somebody their
first blow in this game.
With force, Cassandra gives
Stacy her first knock.
Boo is not wasting any time.
Knocks out Stacy's second tower.
Yau-Man, you're up.
Just like that, Stacy is out of
this challenge.
Have a seat on the bench.
Next question-- who are you
least likely to invite to a
family dinner?
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer-- Boo.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Cassandra got it
right, Mookie got it right,
Dreamz got it right, and Alex
got it right.
Mookie, you're up.
Will we have a repeat?
Will we have a second person
knocked out?
Boo is out of the challenge.
Once again Cassandra gets to
hit.
And knocks out Alex's first
tower.
Next question-- who most has a
sense of entitlement?
Everybody reveal.
The group felt Alex.
Cassandra got it right.
Mookie got it right.
Cassandra, you're up.
Cassandra going right back to
Alex.
Alex now down to his last tower.
Mookie smashes Earl's first
tower.
Next question-- who would you
most like to be stranded on an
island with?
Whose name came up the most
often?
Everybody reveal.
The correct answer is Yau-Man.
Everybody got it right except
Alex.
There is going to be some damage
done in this round.
Earl, you're up first.
Earl nonchalant.
Payback has begun.
Mookie back to Earl.
Dreamz heads to Alex.
Alex is out of this challenge.
Edgardo gives Earl a little
what's up and takes him out of
the challenge.
Yau-Man heads to Edgardo.
Cassandra knocks Mookie's
second tower out.
Okay, Earl and Alex are out of
the challenge.
Take a seat on the bench.
Who do you not want to see again
after the game?
Everybody reveal.
Everybody said Stacy.
Correct answer was Stacy.
Dreamz surveying the field.
Who's going to get his love?
Edgardo heading directly to
Yau-Man's towers.
Yau-Man getting even with
Dreamz.
Mookie going to pay Cassandra
back for her last hit.
Cassandra takes Mookie out of
the game.
Next question-- who smells the
worst?
Out of all the people left in
this game, who smells the worst?
Everybody reveal.
Edgardo thinks he smells the
worse.
Yau-Man thinks Stacy smells the
worst.
Cassandra and Dreamz think
Dreamz smells the worst.
Dreamz is nodding.
He knows.
It is Dreamz.
Cassandra got it right.
And Dreamz got it right.
Cassandra knocks Yau-Man out of
the game.
Just like that, Edgardo down to
his last tower.
Next question-- who mistakenly
believes they are in control of
this game?
Everybody reveal.
The group felt Alex was the
person who mistakenly believed
they were in control of this
game.
Cassandra is right.
Make your move.
Edgardo's out of the game.
He takes a spot on the bench.
We are down to two.
Both have two towers left.
Who has wasted this great
opportunity?
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer is Stacy.
Cassandra got it right.
Make your move.
Cassandra knocks Dreamz's whole
name off the board.
>> Not so hard.
>> PROBST: Dreamz down to his
last tower.
Cassandra get this right, she
wins the challenge.
Athletically, who out here has
surprised you the most in terms
of their athleticism?
Reveal.
Dreamz says Cassandra.
Dreamz is wrong.
Cassandra says Yau-Man.
Cassandra is right.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Take your last hit.
And with that, Cassandra wins
this challenge.
Not one question wrong.
Nice job.
First order of business will not
be fun.
You're sending one person to
Exile Island.
They will stay there until the
next immunity challenge.
Who are you going send off?
>> Mookie.
>> PROBST: Mookie, going back to
Exile Island.
The boat will pick you up.
Head on down to the water.
All right, next part of this
reward's a little more fun.
Here is your boarding pass to
your yacht.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: We'll pick you up at
camp.
You'll return to camp in the
morning, refreshed, some good
food in your belly.
Here are three more boarding
passes.
You are going to decide which
three people join you on this
reward, and you're going to do
it when you get back to your
camp.
>> Okay.
>> I'll lick your feet, man.
>> PROBST: Some negotiating to
be had.
>> Uh-huh.
>> PROBST: All right, guys, grab
your stuff.
Head on back to camp.
>> I am very irritated with
Cassandra.
She just sent me to Exile
Island.
Cassandra is quiet, but in a
deceiving, conniving way.
She just made the worst mistake
of her life.
Given the clues, there has to be
two idols.
The Moto tribe members get the
same exact clues as the Ravu
members.
I mean, if you couldn't find
this on the third clue, you must
be stupid.
Worthless.
Earl came to Exile Island about
five, six times.
Most likely Earl found the other
one.
I'm 99% sure that Earl has the
immunity idol.
Smart guy.
All I want to do is take out
Cassandra and her alliance,
period.
Call it revenge, but I'm gunning
for her.
I just have to get in touch with
the Four Horsemen, and it's
done.
>> Cassandra back in high
school.
The most popular girl
again.
>> I just won my first reward,
first time on a yacht, and I had
a chance to take three people.
Dreamz you may as well come up.
>> What number?
>> Boo, come on up.
>> Oh, yes!
>> Basically my strategy was to
choose people that I needed to
form an alliance with.
Dreamz and Boo, I wasn't sure
where they stood.
Of course, it just gets tougher
as I narrow it down.
Oh, god.
This is hard.
Wow.
I mean, Yau-Man, would you join
me?
>> Thank you.
>> And then the last one was
Yau-Man.
I just think Yau-Man works so
hard, and he needed a break.
>> De plane!
>> Hey, let's go, y'all.
They're honking for us.
>> De plane!
De plane!
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Welcome on board.
>> Well, thank you very much.
The first thing I saw on the
yacht was cheese and crackers
and olives, just an amazing
spread.
That's when it really started
hitting me-- I just won.
Boo, you want a margarita?
>> Yeah, I want a margarita!
>> I felt like "Welcome to the
lifestyle of the rich and
famous."
>> Champagne for you two.
I'll pass them over.
>> Cling-cling, cling-cling.
>> Boo, you're solidly with us.
>> Man, I am solidly...
>> Part of our syndicate.
And, Dreamz, the syndicate.
>> From day one.
>> Let's not make any more
mistakes.
Let's proceed carefully.
We'll go all the way.
>> It was hardball yesterday.
I was like, "Ooh!"
>> There's a lot of work to be
done on Dreamz, a little bit
more, so we can be absolutely
sure we have him on our side.
And this is a way for to us to
solidify it-- feed him, get him
away from everybody.
Just brainwash him, basically.
Cheers.
>> Cheers.
>> So we're all straight with
our alliance?
>> Uh-huh.
Without a doubt.
>> The next one to go is Alex.
>> Uh-huh.
He's playing a Harvard graduate
game.
He's playing hardball.
I think Dreamz is playing both
sides right now, because I can't
sense in his eyes 100%
commitment to our alliance, so I
don't know what the future is
going to be for us with Dreamz.
>> Firecrackers, Joe.
>> I'm the swing vote that's
stuck between the two alliances.
Mookie' plan was to stick with
the old plan and go with the
four boys and Stacy.
But my heart telling me go with
Cassandra, Earl, and Yau-Man and
Boo.
So it's like, so much
information going on that it's
clogging my mind, and I don't
know what to do right now.
It's like I'm being tugged in
every direction except my own.
>> Alex, man, they're going to
use your name.
They'll probably put your name
in the pot tomorrow.
Your name is going to come up
tomorrow.
Man, we messed up.
>> That's the thing.
What about Mookie?
If Mookie don't give you the
idol...
You haven't seen Lord of the
Rings?"
When they get the ring, like,
"My precious..."
>> Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gollum.
>> Yeah.
He's getting like that.
>> I understand.
But I don't want to get knocked
out.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't want you to get knocked
out.
>> Can we get the pot?
We need the pot.
>> Oh, you guys need the pot?
>> You guys are gone forever,
and we don't have that much
wood.
There is a major part of me that
wants to let Dreamz go.
You know, right now I'm trying
to keep it personal between us,
but if you keep on fraternizing
with the people that, you know,
we're talking about getting rid
of, then, you know, you're going
to have to get cut.
>> Who's going?
>> You know...
>> No, just say it.
>> Earl, I mean, he was... he's
not doubting you.
>> It hurt my feelings when you
just said that.
>> No.
>> Come here, Earl.
>> No, let me talk to you.
>> Let me talk to you.
Cassandra told me that you're...
>> I said we're not sure what
camp you're in and we need to
know that you're firm on our
side.
>> You know I heard what y'all
were saying, right?
You know I was standing there.
>> Yeah, yeah.
That's the whole thing.
What did we say?
Earl, I can tell by the way
you're looking at me that you're
doubting me.
>> This is one thing you need to
start doing a little bit more.
>> You don't see the show
enough.
You don't see the show enough to
strategize, because I can tell
you ain't strategizing.
>> I'm someone you need to
listen to more, because I notice
that you talk over us.
Now, we have agreed on this.
>> Mookie's got the immunity
idol.
Yes, Mookie has found the
immunity idol.
Mookie's got the idol.
>> He told you he had it?
>> I seen the idol.
>> What did it look like?
>> It's a turtle.
>> It's a turtle?
>> It's a little turtle
necklace.
>> A turtle necklace?
>> Yeah.
>> So he has the idol?
>> He has the idol.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Why are you just now telling
me this about this idol?
I didn't even know anybody had
it from over there.
I should have been knowing that.
>> Mookie's got it.
>> Dreamz, his problem is he's
trying to do a lot of strategy
on his own, and, yes, it can be
effective, but if you don't tell
people what you're doing, I'm
sorry, I'm just not going to
trust anybody, especially
someone that, you know, has all
these little antics and things
about them that, you know, I
still kind of question anyway.
>> Homebody keep asking Mookie
about the idol.
>> He told everybody he has the
idol?
>> Yeah, him and Alex got the
idol.
>> They found it together?
>> Yes.
>> They didn't fight over it?
>> No.
>> There are two hidden immunity
idols.
The one over here in the Moto
camp was dug up by me.
Dreamz revealed that Mookie
actually have the immunity idol
from Ravu island.
The fact that Mookie have it
made me very nervous, and not
only that, the other two crucial
members, Edgardo and Alex, also
know he has it.
I have to rethink how this will
play out.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Mookie,
returning from Exile Island.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Give it up.
Tribal immunity is no more.
Individual immunity is what you
covet.
You have this around your neck,
you cannot be voted out.
Shall we get to the challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's challenge
you are going to use your arms
to brace between two walls while
your feet are positioned on very
narrow footholds.
Every 30 minutes, you'll step
down to an even smaller
foothold, making it more
difficult.
When you reach the third and
final foothold, you will stay
there for as long as you can.
When you fall off, you're out.
Big rules-- no hips, no back, no
butt.
Arms and feet only.
Last person left standing wins
immunity.
Losers go to tribal council.
Somebody will be going home.
Take your spots.
We'll get started.
This challenge is officially
underway.
Day 27, another hot one.
Not a bit of breeze out here.
Edgardo looks like he could go
all day.
Mookie looks like he might be
asleep he's so comfortable.
>> Ouch!
>> PROBST: Cassandra steps down.
She's the first person out of
the challenge.
Take a spot on the bench.
( drumming )
>> Meke!
Voodoo.
>> Oh, man!
>> PROBST: Out of nowhere,
Edgardo slips off.
And then there were seven.
The foothold you're standing on
now, less than an inch wide.
By the time you get to the
bottom, less than a quarter
inch.
Okay, you've been up there 30
minutes.
It is time to move down one
foothold.
Everybody move.
You are now sitting on a
foothold less than a half an
inch wide.
Mookie looks like a fixed piece
of art.
Mookie slips off, but recovers.
Earl...
>> Slipped.
>> PROBST: ...slipped.
Earl is the third person out of
this challenge.
Who is the odds-on favorite now,
Earl?
>> Stacy.
>> PROBST: Cassandra?
>> PROBST: Edgardo?
>> What I would say right now by
looking at everybody, Stacy.
>> PROBST: Mookie the fourth
person out of this challenge.
Five of you have lasted one
hour.
Everybody step down.
You'll be standing on less than
a quarter inch of wood.
Dreamz struggling.
Alex drops out.
We are now down to Boo, Dreamz,
Stacy, and Yau Man.
Dreamz is out of the challenge.
And we are now down to three
people left.
>> PROBST: After an hour and 15
minutes, Stacy is out of the
challenge.
>> Ooh-wee!
>> PROBST: Boo with a very nice
recovery.
Boo almost loses it, and saves
himself again.
>> How many lives does that guy
have?
>> PROBST: Boo slipping again
and hanging in there.
Boo struggling to recover.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Yau-Man wins first
individual immunity.
>> I'm sure I could stay another
hour.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, come on
over.
Congratulations.
Yau-Man, safe tonight at the
vote.
One of you is going home
tonight.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> All right, it will bring good
luck to everybody.
>> By Cassandra sending me to
Exile Island she ruined the game
for herself and her alliance.
I am going to take out her whole
alliance one by one.
Knowing that Earl potentially
has the idol does change the
game a little bit in terms of
strategy.
You want to get the guy with the
immunity idol, and get him by
surprise.
And hopefully we can take him
out, and take him out with the
immunity idol, and he won't use
it.
>> Hey, look-- I trust you guys.
You're my best bet.
>> When I was on Exile Island I
committed myself to that.
I'm like, "I will not be
faltered.
I will not be wavered by
anybody."
This is the order that we're
sticking with-- Earl, Yau Man,
Boo.
It's done.
>> It's done.
>> Are you 100% on Stacy?
>> Stacy is with us.
She's with us.
>> Are you sure?
>> It's so weird.
We're going go to tribal
council, and I have no idea
what's going on.
I have no idea.
>> But it makes no point if I'm
the only person that's voting
for Alex.
Okay, as long as I have that
assurance.
Then I'll do that to save myself
then.
Are you in?
>> I, of course, want to go with
the majority.
So it's who do I trust more at
this point in the game?
I don't owe anything to Alex.
If saving myself means severing
a tie, then I'll sever that tie.
>> That means she's not in,
dude.
No.
>> What do you think?
I think not.
>> I think... I don't know.
>> Pretty much.
>> You think Mookie is going to
do that?
>> That's the thing.
If Stacy comes through today...
>> Os to show the immunity idol.
>> Show the immunity idol.
All right, well, have that in
line, and have that thing ready
just in case.
>> My hope was that Stacy would
vote with us today to make it
5-3, but it seems like she's not
voting with us anymore.
I don't want to use the immunity
idol this early in the game.
But at the same time, I have to
strategically think about what's
going to get me the furthest in
this game.
I can save Alex by giving him
the immunity idol, but this
early in the game to use the
immunity idol is kind of a
disadvantage.
So things have gotten very
complicated.
>> Mook, Mook, Mook, Mook.
>> Turns out that Mookie gave
the idol to Alex, so we're going
to vote Mookie just to catch
them off guard.
>> Dreamz, Alex, Mookie and I
are voting for Cassandra.
I think that's the smartest
move.
And also, it will be like... you
know, have the hardest punch at
tribal council.
This is an all-or-nothing move.
But if it works out, it will
probably be one of the best
moves ever.
>> I think we should talk about
it between the five of us.
Look, we should do... look, we
should do the five of us for
Edgardo, and not say anything to
anybody else.
That's it.
>> What's going on now is total
chaos.
A lot of people are paranoid.
The panic button has been
pushed.
Mookie had the idol.
He actually gave it to Alex.
So that was from our source,
which is Dreamz, but it could be
a test.
It doesn't matter, because we're
smarter than that, so we won't
vote Alex or Mookie.
We're going to vote Edgardo.
>> Alex, Alex.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Rocky, Lisi, and Michelle, voted
out at the last tribal council.
Okay, Dreamz, was there a mad
scramble when you got back after
the challenge today?
>> Jeff, if you was on that
beach, it was chaotic.
The most chaotic day of any
time-- swing pitchers, swing
voters, swing hitters.
And I'm talking on behalf of
everybody.
It's the most chaotic day ever.
>> I mean, seriously, right now,
I don't even know who the
majority is.
I'm lost.
I'm, like, paranoid.
I've been paranoid ever since...
I mean, I'm paranoid right now.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, the one
guy who doesn't have to be
paranoid tonight is you.
>> This is the first time I've
come to a tribal council meeting
with a regular heart rate and
normal blood pressure.
And that's a good thing for an
old man.
>> PROBST: Mookie, so you're
gone two days, and you come back
to the most chaotic day out
here.
>> Like Edgardo said, tons of
different names coming up.
I'm thinking I'm one of the
people, since I was at Exile.
I don't know what's going on,
either.
But I guess I have to use my own
judgment.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, the way the
idol plays this season is a
little different.
How does that impact how you
vote?
>> If we suspect someone has the
idol, we should try to avoid
voting for that person and vote
somebody in his alliance out
first.
There's two ways to defeat an
army.
One is to cut off the head.
The other is to take away all
the soldiers.
>> PROBST: Alex, how much time
do you spend thinking about the
idol in terms of your strategy?
>> Logically speaking, I'm going
to suspect that the people who
have been to Exile Island, like
Earl, are probably going to have
it.
So that tells me either avoid
Earl or try to take out people
in an Earl's alliance.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, how crazy is
this vote going to be tonight?
>> This vote right here is going
to determine everything in the
game.
It's going to separate the
snakes and rats right here.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
First thing, if somebody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, you would
present it to me after we voted,
but before I read the votes.
Yau-Man, you have individual
immunity.
You can, of course, give that to
somebody if you want to, or you
can hang on to it.
>> I'll hang on to it for
tonight.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man is safe.
You cannot vote for Yau-Man
tonight.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Alex, you're up.
>> A strategic move.
Let's still be friends.
>> Nothing against you, but
better you than me.
Let's see if this works.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Okay, if anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now is the time to do
so.
Alex is playing the hidden
immunity idol.
Alex is immune from tonight's
vote.
All votes cast for Alex do not
count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Cassandra.
Cassandra.
Two votes Cassandra.
That's three votes Cassandra.
Mookie.
One vote Mookie.
Edgardo.
That's three votes Cassandra,
one vote Mookie, one vote
Edgardo.
That's three votes Cassandra,
two votes Edgardo, one vote
Mookie.
Edgardo.
We are tied.
Three votes Cassandra, three
votes Edgardo, one vote Mookie.
Edgardo.
That's four votes Edgardo, three
votes Cassandra, one vote
Mookie.
One vote left.
Tenth person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury,
Edgardo.
You need to bring me your torch.
Edgardo, the tribe has spoken.
Well, Alex played the hidden
immunity idol tonight.
Turns out he didn't need it.
The idol will be rehidden.
New clues will be put out on
Exile Island.
The chaos of tonight's tribal
council is a great reminder that
this game is always in a state
of flux-- something to keep in
the back of your head as you
head into the home stretch of
this game.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp, good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
Dreamz has some explaining to
do.
>> Dude, you turned on us.
>> No, I didn't turn on you all.
>> How do you figure?
>> PROBST: Alex and Mookie
discover that Yau-Man has the
other hidden immunity idol.
>> He has it.
>> PROBST: And a new plan is
born.
>> It's going to feel so great.
That's going to feel so...
>> I'm a little bit disappointed
that Dreamz messed me up in that
vote.
My plan was an all or nothing,
and it didn't work out.
But I tried my best, and to the
guys that voted me off, best of
luck.
There's a couple of people that
don't deserve the million
dollars, but there are a couple
that do, and Cassandra,
hopefully you will get voted off
next because I don't like you
very much.