>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> PROBST: ...at the ailing Ravu
tribe, Yau-Man and Earl were the
only ones that knew that the
immunity idol was hidden at
camp.
>> Yau and I have an upper hand
because we're the only ones that
know that it's even on this
island.
It's time to go hunting for
crab.
>> PROBST: And they worked
together to find it.
>> I'm very excited.
I get a chance to dig.
I don't know for how long.
>> PROBST: But Yau-Man's search
was in vain.
>> Try again.
>> PROBST: Drop your buffs.
>> What?
>> PROBST: Then the game took an
unexpected turn.
>> Mookie.
>> PROBST: Choosing members from
opposing tribes...
>> Come on, Dreamz.
>> PROBST: Maybe the biggest
rivalry thus far just paired up.
...the new tribes were formed.
Yau-Man, who are you going to
take?
>> Stacy.
>> PROBST: Lisi, never good to
be odd person out.
Lisi was left tribeless.
>> I thought this would be like
"I'm out!"
>> PROBST: So you just told
these guys that you're fine
going home.
>> Now would be a good time to
exit.
>> PROBST: Well, for the time
being, you'll be going to Exile
Island.
>> Great, thanks.
>> PROBST: One very big decision
left to make.
Which group is going to live on
the luxurious Moto beach and
which group of people is going
back to Ravu?
The fate of the two tribes was
determined...
Show it.
...when Edgardo pulled the
orange buff of Ravu.
( cheering )
>> Garcon, my breakfast!
>> PROBST: At the new Moto...
>> This is real food.
>> PROBST: Earl, Michelle, and
Yau-Man enjoyed the comforts of
their new home.
>> My world just got turned
upside down and for the better.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: At Ravu...
>> I'm glad that there are no
women here.
>> PROBST: The new tribe of
strong men bonded.
>> You want to have Anthony just
get the fire going, and we'll go
fishing?
>> PROBST: But Anthony was left
behind.
>> Unfortunately, I'm left back
here to tend the fires while the
big men go off, and cookie is
still here at the campfire.
>> PROBST: At a tense immunity
challenge, the physically
inferior Moto Tribe surprised
Ravu when they pushed their way
to victory.
Moto wins immunity!
With tribal council looming...
>> Anthony, where's the flint?
>> PROBST: ...Anthony and Rocky
were on the chopping block.
>> I see myself really far from
being friends or liking Rocky a
lot, because all he would cause
is a lot of turmoil.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
>> You have poor social skills.
>> I got poor social skills?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Anthony and Rocky
faced off.
>> You act like a little girl
sometimes.
>> This is why I don't say
anything.
>> Take the skirt off a little
bit.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: But Anthony was the
one to go.
Anthony, the tribe has spoken.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Five men, I think she'll take
a step back.
I think she just felt threatened
by the other girls on the other
tribe.
>> She was.
Lisi will be joining our tribe
today.
The episode she had during the
last challenge where she was
like "Well, I'm out of here"
does concern me a little bit,
but Lisi's the kind of person
just says what's on her mind at
that moment.
So I'm hoping a couple days on
Exile Island will help her
recant a little bit.
>> Hey!
>> Welcome home, baby!
>> I'm with the boys!
>> How was Exile?
>> Exile, can I just tell you,
it's not as bad as people think.
When I first got to Exile
Island, I cracked up.
I literally broke down.
But that's a great thing,
because when you break down, you
put your pieces back together
again.
It makes you stronger.
>> We thought you was going to
quit on us.
>> Whoo!
Well, I mean, imagine, we're
together for what, 14 days?
And all of a sudden it's like...
I had a breakdown.
I was like, "I'm out of here."
>> That's cool.
>> The dynamics in the tribe are
going to get a little sticky
because Edgardo and Alex and I
are really tight.
And I know that Rocky and Mookie
and even Dreamz might want to
get me out of the way.
Let me tell you something.
I reached, like, this spiritual
enlightenment.
Like, when you sit in one place
for a long time, you start
thinking, like, deep.
So I was, like, tripping, man.
I was up there like...
>> I told you she was going to
fit right in.
Didn't we tell you guys?
>> Back at old Moto, I never
really had a relationship with
Lisi.
I didn't like her.
She didn't like me.
>> Okay, we're officially on
Survivor now, guys.
>> So she should be worried out
of her mind.
( theme song playing )
>> I sleep so light.
I hear everything.
>> The new Moto tribe consists
of three old Ravu, which is
myself, Yau, and Michelle, and
old Moto, which is Cassandra,
Boo, and Stacy.
So now this new Moto is three
and three, so everybody has
three votes.
So we're even.
So... but we need to change the
power here.
I'm going to catch a fish.
Y'all want to go down in the
water a little bit?
>> I just want to get the boat
back.
>> Well, if anything, we can
just go do that, just go bring
the boat.
>> I'm setting something up with
Yau.
There is definitely an idol on
Ravu's camp and Moto's camp.
And we have an idea of exactly
where the immunity idol is here,
but we haven't had the chance to
go get it.
>> Yau-Man is going to stay
behind while the five of us go
retrieve the boat.
So this gives him a moment to
look, and we'll have it.
So that'll be our ace in the
pocket.
>> Right there.
Can you see it?
You can see it now.
>> Oh!
Oh, my God!
This is my... this is it.
This is my million dollars right
here.
I'm glad I'm not in an untying
contest right now, because I
would lose.
The one and only immunity idol.
I know there's another one
somewhere in the other island,
but right now, this is the only
one that exists.
This is mine.
It looks good on me.
It really does.
I'm going to jump out of my skin
here!
Turtle.
My plan now is to let Earl know,
because I owe him that much.
He engineered this whole boat-
saving party for me.
And so I agree to share the use
of this idol when the time comes
with him.
All right, untouched.
Back to work!
>> Yau-Man.
>> Yau, we're back.
>> My arms are falling off.
Did you guys get the boat?
>> No, it's too high up.
We're going to have to wait for
high tide.
>> Oh, well, good try and all
that.
Thank you, y'all.
The sun's not that hot, so I
should have gone out and helped.
>> It wasn't anything we can do.
The boat is so far up on the
rock.
With a net, where I was at, I'll
catch something.
>> Let's see how we can untangle
the net.
When I first came into this
game, I did not have any
expectation of finding a new
friend in such a short time that
I can trust so much.
>> But Earl is different.
His word was good.
I would have never thought that
a big, strong, black man would
become one of my best allies in
this game.
>> What I initially told Yau is
I will help you with the idol
because I knew the value of Yau,
and I knew if I helped this guy,
I could feel it that he would
actually remember that and would
trust me a lot.
>> I went at it so fast.
I was digging furiously.
I mean...
>> Yau having the idol helps
because hopefully there's a
power change.
We'll share this, you know.
If they're trying to vote me
out, he'll let me know, and
he'll give it to me.
And if they're trying to vote
him out, then he'll just use it,
and so that's the way how two
people can share an idol.
>> We'll make it to the final
two if all things align, you
know, Earl.
>> PROBST: Moto, come on in!
Ravu, come on in!
Moto getting your first look at
the new Ravu tribe.
Anthony voted out at the last
tribal council, and this
morning, Lisi joined their
tribe, returning from Exile
Island.
>> She made it.
Wow.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, each tribe will use a
flame thrower to launch
fireballs at three separate
targets.
Each time you hit a target, it
will burst into flames.
First tribe to ignite all three
of their targets wins reward.
You want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Tomorrow morning, the
winning tribe will be picked up
by a seaplane and taken to your
own private Fijian arcade.
A little usual in the middle of
all these islands to find an
arcade, but we did.
So you'll have an afternoon of a
different kind of game playing,
foosball, air hockey, a bowling
alley.
And an afternoon at an arcade
would not be complete without
hot dogs and beer.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will send one
person from the losing tribe to
Exile Island.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
First two throwers, it is Earl
for Moto, Dreamz for Ravu.
>> Come on, Earl!
You got this!
>> You got it, Earl!
( cheering )
>> Hot dogs, Dreamz.
>> PROBST: When you're ready.
Three, two, one, launch.
Earl just short for Moto, inches
short.
Dreamz not messing around,
connects and scores for Ravu.
Ravu leads one-zip.
Next round, it is Michelle for
Moto, Lisi for Ravu.
Three, two, one, launch.
Lisi launches hard but short.
Michelle just misses.
>> Oh, good try!
Good try!
>> PROBST: It's Yau-Man for
Moto, Edgardo for Ravu.
>> You got it!
>> Yau!
>> Show them that secret
technique, Yau.
They don't know.
Show them.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Ravu leads one-zip.
When you're ready, launch.
Edgardo could extend Ravu's
lead.
No luck.
Yau-Man with a great toss.
( cheering )
We are tied, 1-1.
>> PROBST: It's Boo for Moto,
Mookie for Ravu.
We are tied 1-1.
>> Come on, Boo.
You got this.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
toss.
Boo with a big launch, and just
short again for Moto.
Mookie, dead center for Ravu.
Ravu leads 2-1.
>> That was awesome!
That was awesome!
>> PROBST: Next round, Cassandra
for Moto, Alex for Ravu.
With a good toss here, Alex
could give Ravu their first win
as a tribe.
Three, two, one, launch.
Alex, not going to do it with
that toss.
Cassandra with a good toss for
Moto, just misses to the right.
Next round, Stacy for Moto,
Rocky for Ravu.
Ravu leads 2-1.
Three, two, one, toss.
Stacy falls short.
Rocky just short for Ravu.
Going to have to get some air on
these things.
Next round is Earl for Moto,
Dreamz for Ravu.
Dreamz, what are you more
excited about, hot dogs or the
beer?
>> I don't drink, so I got to
say hot dogs.
>> PROBST: Dreamz could win it
for Ravu right here.
Ravu leads 2-1.
When you're ready, toss.
Earl with a big toss, just
short.
Dreamz with a big launch.
Is it enough?
( cheering )
It is!
Ravu wins their first challenge!
( cheering )
>> Oh, Dreamz came through,
baby!
>> PROBST: Ravu, big decision.
You're sending one member of the
Moto tribe to Exile Island.
Who is it going to be?
>> Earl.
>> PROBST: Why Earl?
>> He's been in Exile Island
many times, so we don't want...
you know, we don't want another
person to get another clue.
>> PROBST: Earl heading back to
Exile Island once again.
The boat will pick you up.
You will return in time for the
next immunity challenge.
For once, Moto, I got nothing
for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head on back to camp.
Ravu, get your stuff.
Head on out.
( cheering )
>> This is what I'm talking
about, reward!
>> Whoo, baby!
>> Finally going over that hump,
getting that "w" under our belt,
now we can actually know we got
this.
We're going to replenish
ourselves.
The whole Moto Tribe is going
down.
We're back in this.
>> Yeah!
>> I'll be your host for the
day.
Shall we go in now?
>> Yeah!
>> Wow.
>> Air conditioning!
>> Oh, they got cheese!
>> Ooh!
>> Oh!
>> Wow!
>> As soon as we saw the food,
it was like a feeding frenzy,
man.
>> Life is good.
>> Life is great!
>> Great!
>> Cheers, guys.
>> Cheers.
>> Cheers to Ravu, many
victories.
>> You know this.
>> Man, I can't wait to get full
so we can play some games.
>> The question of the day is
how much food can you shove in a
pie hole?
They're just shoving like four
hot dogs in their mouth.
I'm like, "Chill out, boys.
Relax.
You'll give yourself a
stomachache."
>> Oh, man.
>> Ow.
( burping )
>> Just to let you know, on the
other side, we have a golf area.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Nice.
>> Cool, virtual golf.
>> Behind you, you have a pool
table.
In front of you, you have a
bowling alley.
>> All right!
>> Whoa!
>> Strike!
>> It's my favorite kind of
scenario.
I love being surround by guys.
To me, being around a bunch of
boys is my favorite place to be,
straight up.
>> All right, she's on my team.
>> Lisi doesn't hold back.
She's like one of the guys.
She just went straight at the
food, the beer.
I mean, she's the type of girl
you'd go to a football game,
chug a beer, bump chests, you
know, every touchdown.
>> Yeah!
Hey, I'm next.
>> Well, when I first got here,
obviously, I'm the chick, so I
would be the weakest link right
there.
( laughter )
But after the win, all the guys
are feeling good.
Whoa!
So they're more accepting.
They've gotten to know me
better, so they can see how I
could really fit in with the
guys.
All right, killer.
No, that's a pretty swing.
>> Everything about me is
pretty.
>> The whole dynamics of the
game is just beginning to shift
daily, so we'll see what
happens, man.
>> It's my third time here.
It's just boring, no big deal.
The idol has been found, so
there's no purpose of getting a
clue.
No one's been here as much as
myself.
I'm going to officially change
the name to Earl Island.
I'll be accepting reservations
for tourism.
You have a nice view of the
ocean, plenty of room to lay
down, good eats.
Just like the finest
restaurants.
Yeah, this is my island.
Lodging isn't very good, but
it's a beautiful view.
Earl's island in Fiji.
>> Man, I just ate way too much
food.
Oh, god!
>> This is horrible.
What have we done?
>> Alex?
>> What?
>> Hurry up, man.
>> So two franks and another hot
dog and then a brownie and a
little bit of beer to wash it
all down with.
And oddly enough, felt kind of
sick.
>> Oh, god!
>> Those brownies were so good
today.
>> Oh, shush!
>> Can we not talk about it
right now?
>> Oh, how come... listen, how
come when I'm starving, right,
I'm sitting on the grass and the
dirt, everyone's talking about
chocolate chip ice cream.
You know, now they're all
rolling on the couch.
"Ah, my stomach."
So I started making fun of them.
"Oh, I'm going to eat 19 hot
dogs, and I'm going to eat 17
brownies."
They were running their mouth.
Now I'm full.
I feel great now.
Now yous all got stomachaches,
and now I can't talk about
brownies and stuff that I had
earlier today.
That's not fair.
People call me up on my own
stuff all the time.
I just think it's fair game, you
know?
And if you can't take stuff like
that here, you shouldn't be
here.
>> This is terrible.
>> I told you.
Everyone's hurting.
You guys better be ready for the
challenge soon.
I don't care.
>> You know what?
I'd rather have this feeling
than have the feeling of
starving.
>> Okay, well, then suck up the
stomachache and shut up then.
>> Rocky, he just doesn't fit in
with us.
We're pretty laid-back guys.
We make fun of each other, but
to a certain extent.
But Rocky takes it to another
level.
I think I gained, like, three
pounds.
>> Three pounds of stomachache
is what you gained.
>> Because he criticizes
everybody, and he's too harsh on
people, and people don't respect
that.
People don't want a guy to be
criticizing you all the time.
That's why they have, like,
bosses and teachers back at
home.
>> Listen, you've been crying
about this for three weeks.
You got what you wanted.
You went a little too crazy too
fast.
Suck it up.
( Rocky laughing )
>> We lost the reward challenge,
and it proved to us that we need
to step up our game if we want
to keep this immunity idol.
It's very important to each and
every one of us here.
Some of us, it's more important
than they really understand.
I mean, it's more important to
Yau than he knows, because if we
lose, he's gone tonight, because
he's got to be the weakest
physically out of all of us.
That's good.
>> Now things are definitely
looking up.
I'm in an alliance with Earl,
who is very strong and a very
honorable man.
I have the immunity idol, and if
I can make it through the merge,
I can go quite far.
My first priority is not let
anybody know that I got the
immunity idol.
Then I have a really evil
thought.
I thought what if there is
another immunity idol for them
to find?
So I start out making my own
immunity idol out of a half
coconut shell.
Basically, I took a coconut
shell.
I paint it with a little face,
and I painted eyebrows.
And just in case they don't know
it's an immunity idol, I put the
initials "I.I." on it.
There are so many immunity idols
running around here.
I made that.
I wrapped it back up.
And when I see that Michelle and
Stacy was falling asleep in bed,
I went quickly and buried it
back in that hole.
I didn't bury it very deep, so
it's easier to find.
So I'm hoping that someone will
decide to hunt for the idol and
we'll have one too many idols
running around, except I have
the official one.
This upcoming immunity challenge
is very important to me.
I'm always the target, but I do
have the immunity idol.
If we lose this immunity
challenge, then I will have to
really keep my ears to the
ground and listen to see if I am
up.
If I am, then I will be forced
to use it, but I really hope I
do not need to use it.
>> PROBST: How's everybody
doing?
>> Good.
>> Good, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Let's get to it.
We'll now bring in Earl
returning once again from Exile
Island.
( applause )
>> Earl!
>> I'm back, feeling good.
>> PROBST: First thing's first,
take back immunity.
Thanks, Michelle.
Once again, immunity back up for
grabs.
For today's challenge, one
person will be your caller.
The rest of the tribe will be
blindfolded.
One at a time, the caller will
lead you out into a field where
there are five skulls hanging.
Using a Fijian war club, you
must smash a skull, releasing a
bundle of tiles.
Then, while still blindfolded,
you must find the tiles and take
them to your puzzle board.
Then race back to the start, and
the next person goes.
Once you've collected all five
bundles of tiles, as a tribe,
you have to unscramble the
puzzle to decipher a two-word
phrase.
First tribe to correctly solve
it wins immunity, guaranteed a
one-in-11 shot at a million
bucks.
>> All right!
>> That's what I'm talking about
>> PROBST: Losers, tribal
council tonight, somebody going
home.
If at some point during the
challenge, you want to switch
out callers, you're allowed to
do so.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize, and we'll get
started.
Here we go.
Michelle is the caller for Moto,
Lisi the caller for Ravu.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
>> All right, Stacy, you're
good.
Follow that rail.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Three more paces, and you'll
feel the pole.
All right, slide right, slide
right.
>> Back, back, Alex, back.
Back, to your left, baby, to
your left.
>> It's right above you.
Do you feel it?
>> PROBST: Stacy takes the first
smash.
>> Hands on the floor.
Hands on the floor.
Forward, forward.
By your knee, by your knee.
There you go.
Okay, go forward, go forward.
Go forward, go forward.
Go forward.
The table's in front of you.
Do you feel it?
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Alex is swing all
over the place but not
connecting.
>> Let it stop swinging.
The skull is on the ground,
Alex.
>> It's on the ground?
>> Yes.
>> Where is it?
>> Move to your left, to your
left.
Forward, forward, forward.
Right there.
Okay, you got it.
You got it.
>> Come on, girl, a little
faster, a little faster.
>> PROBST: Stacy's back for
Moto.
Cassandra on the course.
>> All right, there you go!
>> PROBST: Alex has it, and he's
heading back.
>> Don't hit the... don't hit...
don't hit...
>> PROBST: Alex is back.
>> Switch.
>> PROBST: Ravu going to switch
out callers.
Lisi is done.
Alex is taking over.
>> Go straight, straight, go!
Go, Ed, go.
Keep going, Ed.
>> Come on, girl!
Yeah!
All right, hands on the floor,
hands on the floor!
Right in front of you.
Forward, forward, forward,
forward.
>> Ooh, I got it!
>> There you go, that's it.
Straight in front of you.
>> Okay, okay!
>> Almost.
You got it!
Go down on your knees.
It's on the floor, right next to
your stick.
You got it, you got it!
Ed, get up.
>> Okay, where?
>> Forward, forward, forward!
You got it!
Run back, Ed, run back!
>> Ten paces, come back, come
back!
>> PROBST: Cassandra back.
Earl out on the course.
Edgardo now back for Ravu.
>> Forward, Dreamz, forward.
>> PROBST: We are tied 2-2.
>> To your right, slide right,
slide right.
There you go.
That's where it is, baby!
Yeah!
>> Dreamz, stop, stop!
Move to your left!
One step.
Right above you.
You got it!
Get on your knees.
Right next to the stick.
Follow the stick with your left
hand.
You got it!
>> PROBST: Earl is back.
Boo looking for that club.
Boo now out on the course.
>> Come on, come on, come on!
Yeah, Boo, keep going!
>> You got it Dreamz.
Come back, forward!
Dreamz, run, run, run, run, run!
Straight!
You got it, Dreamz!
>> PROBST: Dreamz is back.
Rocky now out on the course for
Ravu.
>> Rock, go, forward, forward,
forward!
You've got a long way to go,
buddy.
>> Come on, left, left, left,
left!
Your left!
Other side, other side.
>> This way?
>> Yes, that way.
That's your left!
Right there!
Give it a swing!
Come on, Boo, you don't have to
hit it that hard.
Just hit it a little.
There you go!
Hands on the floor, hands on the
floor!
There, that's where it is.
>> Forward half a step.
Smash!
There you go!
It's on the floor.
Right behind your left foot.
Right next your left foot.
You got it!
Turn around, forward, Rock,
forward, forward!
There you go.
Run back!
>> PROBST: Boo is back.
Moto has one bundle left.
>> Faster, Yau-Man, faster,
faster!
Follow that rail.
You're doing awesome.
Follow that rail!
>> Forward, Mookie, right hand,
go!
>> PROBST: Mookie working for
that last skull for Ravu.
>> Okay, go forward, go forward,
Yau-Man!
Yau-Man, go forward!
Yau, stop!
Yau-Man, stop!
>> Hey, you want to switch,
Michelle?
I got a loud voice.
>> PROBST: Moto switching out,
Boo going to become the caller.
Both teams have one bundle left.
>> Tell me where it is.
>> I'm blind right now.
Hold on.
>> Run, run, run, stop!
To your right!
To the right!
Again, again!
>> Yau, to your left.
Now hit down.
Get them down!
Down on your knees!
Right in front of you!
By your knees!
>> PROBST: Yau-Man has the last
bundle.
>> Turn 180, 180.
>> PROBST: He's got to get it on
the puzzle table.
>> Left, left, left, on the
fence!
Left, on the fence!
>> PROBST: He does.
He's got to get back now.
>> Come back, Yau!
>> One half step forward,
Mookie.
Right there, smash it!
>> It's right below you!
Get on your hands and knees,
Mookie!
Stop!
It's right in front of you,
right next to the stick.
Turn around, stop!
>> Come back, Yau!
Keep on, keep on!
>> PROBST: Yau Man back.
Take off your blindfolds!
Go!
Moto has all bundles!
They're now working on the
puzzle!
>> Mookie, run!
Forward, forward!
>> PROBST: Mookie takes a hard
hit into the side of the course.
>> To your left, to your left,
to your left!
Forward, forward, forward!
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfolds!
Ravu has all five bundles!
They're now working on the
puzzle.
It is a two-word phrase.
>> "Castaway," "castaway,"
"castaway."
>> There's no w.
It's not "castaway."
>> Where is Michelle?
>> Yes?
"Cannibal," "cannibal,"
"cannibal."
>> "Cannibalism," "cannibalism."
>> We're ready.
>> PROBST: Moto thinks they have
it.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> PROBST: "Cannibal Isles" is
correct!
Motto wins immunity!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Moto,
congratulations.
>> Yeah.
( applause )
>> PROBST: You still have not
lost an immunity challenge,
nobody in danger of going home
tonight.
Ravu, unfortunately not the same
case.
One of the six of you will be
voted out at tonight's tribal
council.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> We lost today.
We're going to have to vote
somebody out.
Alex and I figured out that we
don't need really strong
players.
You know, once we get closer to
the merger, if there's a merger,
what we need is people that are
loyal, and Lisi is one of those
people.
I know Rocky's counting on
getting Lisi out, but, I mean, I
think his head is next.
>> Rocky, I don't trust him that
much.
>> I don't trust Rocky.
>> I don't know if we should
tell Mookie or not, because he's
tight with Rocky.
>> Don't talk to him.
>> But Rocky's out.
I can't... I mean, I like the
guy, but I can't... he's... last
night he was just...
>> Too much.
>> Rocky has just this bad vibe
about him, and I think one of
the reasons that Ravu didn't
ever win was his attitude about
stuff.
Lisi, Alex, and I were from the
other tribe, and she knows that
she has to be loyal to us
because she doesn't have anybody
else to tag along with.
It's you, me, and Edgardo.
>> I know this.
>> So even if we get whittled
down, the three of us are
straight.
>> For real, for real.
>> So Rocky goes next, okay?
>> Okay.
>> And Ed and I were talking.
He had kind of a good idea.
I want to know your thoughts on
it.
Okay, we need to figure out who
has got the damn immunity idol.
>> Let me tell you something
right now.
The idol's on this island.
It's here.
>> Right.
>> It's not on Exile.
I think that with the clues that
I have, you, me, and Edgardo
should start prowling around the
island.
>> Yeah.
>> I think we're better off if
we try to spread this than just
me trying to be greedy trying to
find the idol, so...
>> Right, I agree.
>> Take me to the water so I can
rinse off my freaking socks.
>> All right, let's go.
>> The story with the idol is
there's some clues that I could
go on which lead me to believe
that it might be here, but it's
all really vague.
What I'm going to do with the
idol is have Edgardo and Alex
help me.
>> What do these clue say?
>> It might be right underneath
this big cave, underneath where
people sleep.
>> Okay.
>> So it might be... it might be
underneath the palm fronds.
We'll see what happens.
You know, I have no choice but
to believe Alex at this point.
But that being said, this game
turns and twists, and people say
one thing and do another.
>> For real?
That's what they're telling you?
>> Yeah.
>> Here's the thing.
Would you guys care if you guys
all voted him and then I just
voted, like, just someone?
Because I...
>> Yeah, no, I wouldn't care.
I'd probably vote with you.
>> Dreamz told me that Alex and
Edgardo were talking about
sending off Rocky before Lisi.
Well, that leaves only one of
previous Ravu, and they're just
going to wipe us out.
I got have to figure out a way
to turn it around, and I think
right now my man Dreamz, I trust
him.
I think he was left out in the
other previous tribe, and so the
opportunity to, you know, align
myself with himself is the best
thing I can do.
>> Me and Rocky's personality,
we don't bump heads like it
appeared that it would, because
I understand Rocky.
That's how... that's who he is.
That's how he talks, you know
what I mean?
That don't mean that he's mad at
you and want to fight you, you
get what I'm saying?
>> Yeah.
>> I think Rocky knows that he's
on the chopping block tonight.
Some of the boys think, "Hey,
he's got a bad attitude; he's
got to go."
>> What's everybody crying
about?
>> Losing today.
>> Just got to win tomorrow.
>> Rocky throws a lot of false
attitude, but it's not real
attitude.
It's not the real way he feels.
It's just his personality.
>> Right?
>> We have to win tomorrow.
>> Yeah.
>> I never really got the chance
to know Rocky.
I would really like to get to
know Rocky.
So I feel I would rather Lisi
leave if somebody was to leave,
because then we'll still be
strong, but just without Lisi.
>> I hate tribal council.
What do you think, bitch?
>> I think you should ( no
audio ) push over a little bit,
unless you want to make out with
me ( no audio ).
To be honest with you, I've been
a little nervous today.
Out of all the tribal councils,
I was the one pulling the
strings in all the other ones.
That's not the case this time.
>> Yeah.
>> I think Lisi's definitely
going to go home, but who knows?
I could go home today.
>> Going into tribal is going to
be like a cliffhanger situation,
because even though we've all
talked that I'm not going to get
voted out, you never know what
happens at the last minute.
>> PROBST: So let's start with
Lisi.
When you weren't selected to be
on either tribe, you had
somewhat of a meltdown.
>> Yeah, sure.
I was looking forward to going
home.
I thought that was my exit.
>> PROBST: So when you came back
to this tribe, you had to be a
little uneasy about how you
would be welcomed.
>> Um, I knew I was going to go
back to a tribe that contained
people from my old tribe, so I
was really not concerned about
general consensus of the tribe
towards me, because I knew I was
going to find a friend wherever
I went.
And from that thread, I would
just, you know, start bringing
myself up.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, you watched
Lisi out there.
What was your reaction?
>> Well, at first, when Lisi had
the breakdown, I knew that she
just wanted to quit the game.
And I was like, "Man, we got to
win so we don't have to get
Lisi," because I didn't want her
on our team if she was wanting
to go home.
But when she came back and she
wasn't the same way she was when
I seen her with the breakdown, I
was happy about that, and I knew
that we were ready for business.
>> PROBST: Rocky, what's the
feeling as tribal council starts
to approach?
Is everybody scurrying around,
trying to make sure it's not
them?
>> I think it's in the back of
people's minds, because you
know, we just... we're a tight
group, but we're a new group,
you know what I mean?
So I think everyone's a
little... not really nervous,
but it's always in the back of
everybody's minds exactly what's
going on.
>> PROBST: So, Mookie, this
tribe's strength being its
physical strength and agility,
how does that factor in to who
you get rid of?
>> It's hard choosing which
person is going to go, because
we're all so strong.
And Lisi over here brings
another aspect.
Maybe we need a girl.
So it makes it really difficult
trying to figure out who to let
go, because this whole physical
thing hasn't really been working
in our favor so far.
So you have to look at it both
ways, and I really don't know.
>> PROBST: Rocky, can you trust
these guys to be telling you the
truth as we get ready to vote?
>> Basically, you know what?
I'm going with my gut right now.
I trust certain people.
That's all I can do.
And then I just got to read
everybody else, you know, see
what I can do.
>> PROBST: Lisi, does this tribe
need to make any adjustments?
You get up tomorrow morning;
what's the first thing you're
going to do?
>> Look around and be like,
"Ooh, God, I'm still here?"
( laughing )
Yeah, pretty much.
We need to win.
Whatever happens, we need to
win.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
the vote.
If, at this point, somebody has
found the hidden immunity idol,
and you need to play it tonight,
you would present it to me
before I read the votes.
It is time to vote.
Rocky, you're up.
>> Because that's the way it's
got to go.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and they want to
play it, now is the time to do
so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
First vote, Lisi.
Lisi.
Rocky.
Two votes Lisi, one vote Rocky.
Two votes Lisi, two votes Rocky.
Rocky.
That's three votes Rocky, two
votes Lisi.
One vote left.
Seventh person voted out and the
first member of our jury, Rocky.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Get it, boys, huh?
>> PROBST: Rocky, the tribe has
spoken.
>> Be good, boys, huh?
>> PROBST: Well, based on what I
heard tonight, Rocky had no idea
that was coming.
If it could happen to him, it
can happen to you.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> I'm going to cry.
>> PROBST: ...things get tough
for Lisi.
>> This sucks.
>> PROBST: The tribes learn a
new skill.
>> Boo is doing the whole white
guy thing.
>> PROBST: And at Ravu...
>> We should just tear this
place all apart.
>> PROBST: ...the hunt for the
idol gets dirty.
>> We're digging for the idol
while Lisi and Dreamz are
sleeping.
>> Ah!
I'm extremely pissed off.
I'm angry.
They got me good, man.
They got me really good.
I didn't see anything coming.
Then all of a sudden, boom, I
get smacked in the mouth way
cinder block.
But you know what?
Now I get to be on the jury, and
hopefully none of those cats get
the million bucks thanks to me.