>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Lisi returned from Exile
Island...
>> Welcome home, baby!
>> PROBST: ...and joined the new
all-male Ravu tribe.
>> Back at Moto, I didn't like
her, she didn't like me.
So she should be worried.
>> I'm with the boys!
>> PROBST: She didn't realize
that Alex, Edgardo, Dreamz, and
Mookie had already formed a
tight alliance of four.
At the new Moto, Yau-Man
discovered the hidden immunity
idol.
>> This is my million dollars!
>> PROBST: And he realized
another one existed on Ravu's
beach.
>> I know there's another one
somewhere on the other island.
>> PROBST: At a fiery reward
challenge...
Dreamz with a big launch.
Is it enough?
It is!
Dreamz secured a victory for
Ravu.
Ravu wins their first challenge!
And they were whisked away to a
remote arcade, where they gorged
on hot dogs, beer, and brownies.
>> As soon as we saw the food it
was like a feeding frenzy, man.
This is terrible.
>> PROBST: And then paid the
price.
>> I just ate way too much food.
>> You guys better be ready for
the challenge soon.
>> PROBST: Rocky showed no
sympathy.
>> You got what you wanted.
Suck it up.
>> Follow the rail!
Follow the rail!
>> PROBST: At an injury-laden
immunity challenge...
>> Mookie, run!
>> Cannibal, cannibal.
>> PROBST: ...Moto again claimed
immunity.
Cannibal Island is correct!
Moto wins immunity!
And Ravu was forced to choose
yet another tribemate to leave
the game.
>> I hate going to tribal
council.
>> What do you think?
>> I think you should ( bleep )
push over a little bit unless
you want to make out with me.
>> PROBST: Rocky's attitude had
him on the bubble.
>> Rocky has just this bad vibe
about him, and I think one of
the reasons that Ravu didn't
ever win was his attitude about
stuff.
>> The idol is on this island.
It's here.
>> PROBST: And in order to save
herself, Lisi revealed clues to
the whereabouts of the hidden
idol.
>> With the clues I have, you,
me, and Edgardo should start
prowling around the island.
>> Alex and I figured out that
we don't need really strong
players.
What we need is people that are
loyal.
>> PROBST: At tribal council...
The seventh person voted out and
the first member of our jury.
...Rocky was blindsided and
become the first member of our
jury.
Rocky, the tribe has spoken.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Edgardo and I are sort of in
between a couple alliances.
It seems like he and I are
aligned with Mookie and Dreamz
on the one hand, and we're
aligned with Lisi on the other
hand.
Edgardo and myself had a
previous alliance with her when
we were all part of Moto.
So right now I feel like I'm in
a pretty good place.
After Lisi got back from Exile
Island, she told Alex and me two
clues.
One of the clues was "It's at
the highest point in the island.
Dig down."
And the other clue said, "Dig
beneath where you sleep."
So myself, Alex, and Edgardo
were digging for the idol while
Lisi and Dreamz were sleeping.
>> A little left, six inches.
Right there.
>> I know that myself, Dreamz,
Edgardo, and Alex made a pact
together.
But I need to figure out how I'm
going to secure my space within
this trust.
I was digging in the right place
at the right time, and I don't
know how they didn't hear that,
but I got the immunity idol.
Hopefully it's smooth sailing
from here.
>> Lisi let us in on basically
all the clues to find the
immunity idol.
So we started digging, we
adjusted a little bit, and lo
and behold, the three of us
found it while everyone else was
asleep.
>> There is no words to describe
how much this means to me in
this game.
So to bring this back, it holds
my position for sure.
>> The reason we didn't tell
Lisi is because even though she
is really loyal, she's an
unstable person.
We were afraid that if we told
her, she would want to use it
the wrong way, just because I
don't think Lisi is a very smart
person playing the game.
>> Don't tell Dreamz.
>> Don't tell him until it's
necessary.
>> We're not telling Dreamz
about the immunity idol because
he's very close with Cassandra,
and if there is a merge, he may
have just a flareup of, like,
complete honesty and tell
Cassandra, tell who knows what
about the immunity idol.
And once they know we have it,
its effect is gone.
>> You can say that myself, Alex
and Edgardo have the idol, but
in my mind, it's in one pocket,
and that's in my pocket.
>> A little idol digging?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's where I suspect
it is, right around there.
It's got to be right here where
we're sleeping.
I suspect Alex told Mookie that
the idol is right where we
sleep.
Because this morning Mookie
tried to be, like, a little
discreet, flipping leaves and
trying to play with the ground,
and I was like, "What, idol
digging?"
And he had no choice but to say,
"Uh, yeah."
I'm like, "Dude, you're going to
have to wake up really, really
early to fool an old cat like
me.
What's wrong with you?"
>> I have the idol, and Lisi is
still digging for it.
She has no idea.
And I'm going to help her dig.
And that's the funny part.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Hola.
>> Great, you guys, come on with
us!
>> Today, you will learn a
traditional Fijian miki, a
dance.
>> Oh, my god!
>> The skilled Fijian dancers
are here to teach you how to do
it.
They will instruct you for two
hours.
>> You will compete against the
other tribe this afternoon and
try to outdance them at a local
village.
The winners stay for a feast at
the village.
>> It looks like we have a
dance-off competition with Ravu
today.
And we had some Fijian dancers
come and school us.
And then if we win we get a nice
spread of food.
>> We have to sit one person
out.
>> One person out.
>> I'm all knees here when
dancing.
>> Well, you're sitting out.
>> When it comes to dancing, I
have absolutely no rhythm.
I can't keep the beat if my life
depends on it.
>> I got the moves.
I got the moves.
You know, I had to pull out some
of my Michael Jackson moves, you
know?
They put me up front, and I'm
ready to take the lead.
>> That's a little too much
hips, Boo.
>> It was funny seeing Boo, you
know?
Boo was doing the whole... the
white guy thing.
But he hung in there, and he's
making a great effort at it.
I think we'll be okay.
>> Size, strength, and agility
is not necessarily going to be
an advantage on this one.
There's no way Yau-Man and those
girls are going to beat us at
this.
I mean, it's kind of
frustrating, right?
Because we've lost twice to a
bunch of girls and an old guy.
If we don't all work in unison,
we don't eat.
>> ( speaking in Fijian
language )
>> Okay.
Okay.
>> Challenges, honestly, I don't
take seriously.
I don't think we should be out
here brooding about "We've got
to win," or "We've got to eat
that food!"
I mean, come on, guys.
>> I really don't like Lisi.
Lisi was one of the reasons that
I was so miserable at Moto.
Every challenge she's done has
been horrible.
So Lisi should be worried,
because she's the weakest, and
we're trying to get to the merge
with numbers up.
If we lose a challenge, she will
be the next person voted off.
>> PROBST: Moto, come on in!
Moto looking good.
Ravu, come on in!
Moto getting your first look at
the new Ravu tribe.
Rocky voted out at the last
tribal council.
He became the first member of
the jury.
Everybody go ahead and have a
seat.
Glad to see everybody has
embraced today so far.
>> For real.
>> PROBST: Are you guys ready to
get to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, this
morning you were taught a meke,
which is a traditional dance.
Today you will get the
opportunity to perform this meke
in front of some Fijian judges.
You will be judged on three
criteria-- your appearance,
authenticity, and, of course,
spirit.
Did you embrace the dance?
Our judges are all experts in
Fijian dance.
They will determine the winner.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Your reward is a
Fijian feast-- it is cooking
right now in a lovo-- of
chicken, pork, seafood.
You'll also enjoy some nice
Fijian singing.
In addition, the winning tribe
will send one member of the
losing tribe to Exile Island.
They will return in time for the
next immunity challenge.
Shall we get to it?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Moto, you have one
extra tribe member.
You had to decide this morning
who was going to sit out.
Based on how you guys look,
I'm guessing it was Yau-Man.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Moto, you are up.
( chanting )
>> Meke!
( applause )
>> PROBST: Nicely done.
Have a seat back on your mat.
Ravu, the stage is yours.
( chanting )
>> Argh!
( applause )
>> PROBST: Nicely done.
Have a seat.
Give the judges a chance to
discuss.
( inaudible conversation )
You guys have made a decision?
>> Yes, Jeff.
>> PROBST: All right, tell me
first about Moto.
What did they do well and what
could they have improved on?
>> Moto, first of all, their
appearance, as Ravu, is good,
the way they dressed themselves
up.
>> PROBST: So both tribes you
thought did a good job?
>> Yes, they did a good job on
their appearance.
And also the spirit on both
teams were there.
>> PROBST: So you liked the
appearance equally.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: And you liked spirit
equally?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: So it's going to come
down, as it should, to how well
they did the actual dance.
>> Yes.
The actual dance, for Moto, the
group was... you know, they were
better organized.
And I think the leader was
really good.
Whereas Ravu, their body
movement was out of rhythm with
the chant.
They were either too fast again
or behind in their actions.
When it comes down to the final
point of coordination, I think
Moto...
>> PROBST: Judges, thank you
very much.
First thing we have to do, Moto,
somebody going directly to Exile
Island.
Who is it going to be?
>> Lisi.
>> PROBST: Lisi going back to
Exile Island.
Why Lisi, Earl?
>> So no one else will get any
clues.
>> All right, then.
>> PROBST: Lisi, the boat will
pick you up.
You'll be back in time for the
next immunity challenge.
All right, Ravu.
Unfortunately, I've got nothing
for you.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
Okay, Moto, you're going to
enjoy an authentic Fijian feast
that's been cooking for hours
especially for you.
Some singing, and it starts now.
>> One thing about being part of
this game, we haven't had a
chance to experience what's
here-- you know, the beauty of
Fiji and the people and the
natives.
We don't know anything.
And that was the first time we
got to actually absorb the
culture, and that's fascinating
to me.
>> Oh, my god!
It's so beautiful!
>> My mouth is, like, watering
right now.
The feast was the one of the
most incredible things that I've
ever experienced.
There were huge lobsters.
They had chicken, big pieces of
papaya.
We were eating with both our
hands.
It was just amazing-- the food,
the people, it was just
incredible.
Oh, my god, there's watermelon.
>> True feast here, baby.
>> Oh, my god, this is amazing.
>> It was incredible.
These people have such huge
hearts.
I don't think that any one of us
will ever forget this for the
rest of our lives.
>> A night like this brings us
closer together, because we were
still kind of separated.
You know, it was still kind of
some old Ravu and old Moto.
I mean, we still hadn't
connected all the way.
And I think a celebration like
this feels good as a group, that
we can finally push forward and
keep going as a solid group now.
This time it's our turn in the
sun, and I'm happy.
>> The game just gets so dark
sometimes.
Ravu just can't seem to win even
the simplest challenges.
This is kind of serious for
someone that likes to take it
light.
It sucks that I'm here.
I mean, like, look at me-- I'm a
moment away from crying.
I don't want to be here.
This sucks.
I really don't want to be here.
But what am I supposed to do,
man?
This sucks.
There's only so much of this I
can take.
I don't want to let down Alex
and Edgardo, but I feel like
quitting.
>> Michelle and I have our usual
morning meetings, because I'm
usually the first person up, and
then she gets up pretty soon,
and everyone else is always just
laying there.
So we always get up, and she
briefs me on what's happening,
because she is my little spy.
I think, Boo, if you put Boo in
the right situation, he'll be
with us.
>> Uh-huh, yeah.
>> But I still wasn't sure,
because Cassandra said Boo is
dangerous.
If Boo makes the merger he'll be
the most dangerous.
I don't know.
>> Stacy's got that fourth card.
>> She wants to do that.
And that's what makes her a
little more dangerous because
her vote's going to switch.
>> That's why I feel like Stacy
first, because that will scare
Boo and get him on our side.
>> Yeah.
>> Earl and I are targeting
Stacy.
She still does have ties on the
other side, particularly with
Alex.
Ideally we'd want to get rid of
Stacy before the merge, because
that's when we feel like she'll
be most dangerous.
>> One of those two has to go at
the next immunity.
>> I feel like it will have to
be Stacy.
I am afraid that the longer
Stacy sticks around, the more in
danger it put me, because me and
Stacy are kind of carbon copies
of each other when it comes down
to function.
I don't think there's enough
room for the both of us.
>> We've got to get out of this
losing spirit.
>> I'm feeling confident, still.
I'm pretty sure tomorrow we're
going to merge.
>> Right now I'm really worried
that Dreamz might be tight with
Cassandra, and he might flip
over.
So I think I am going to keep my
eye on him because I know he is
going to be a threat.
>> This is pretty cool.
>> Interesting...
>> All right.
"Everybody gets their shot.
It's immunity you desire.
Ready, aim, make it count.
Tonight, somebody loses fire."
>> We need the next immunity
bad.
Going into a merge 4-6, much
harder than 5-5.
>> Ever shot a bow and arrow?
>> Yeah.
>> I haven't.
>> It's all about keeping your
arm straight.
>> When you release, you just
release your backhand like that
completely.
>> I never say I'm pretty good
at stuff, but I'm pretty good at
archery, I think.
>> Go for the harder shots,
whatever the hell they are.
>> I'm pretty sure of this
challenge because have a lot of
confidence in my archery
abilities.
I've been kind of low key in all
the challenges, just doing my
role, listening to people.
And I feel like this is my time
to shine.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Lisi
returning from Exile Island.
>> What's going on, kids?
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Take back the immunity idol.
You've got to let it go.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
you will test your skills with
three different weapons.
First round is blow darts.
Each tribe member will get one
shot.
Whoever ends up closest to the
bull's eye scores one point for
their tribe.
Second round, you will throw
spears.
Closest to the bull's eye is
worth two points.
For the final round, you will
shoot a bow and arrow.
Closest to the bull's eye scores
three points for your tribe.
The tribe with the most points
wins immunity.
Losers will go to tribal
council, and for somebody, the
dream of winning this game will
come to an end.
Moto, you have one extra member.
Who are you going to sit out?
>> I will.
>> PROBST: Cassandra takes a
spot on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize and we'll
get started.
First round is blow darts.
Closer to the center of the
bull's eye scores a point for
your tribe.
Lisi first up.
She set the mark to beat.
Stacy up for Moto.
Moto now has the mark to beat.
>> There you go!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Ravu up.
Mookie just inside of Stacy's
dart.
Ravu now has the mark to beat.
Moto back up.
Not enough lung capacity.
Dreamz trying to improve on
Mookie's shot.
And he does!
Yau-Man with a nice shot!
Moto now has the mark to beat.
Alex for Ravu.
Ravu back in the lead.
First round has been back and
forth.
Boo takes the lead back for
Moto!
Comes down to Edgardo for Ravu.
Ravu's last shot.
If Edgardo doesn't get this,
Moto wins the round, Earl
doesn't have to go.
And he does not.
Moto wins first round and the
first point.
Next round, throwing spears.
This round is worth two points.
Moto leads one point-zero.
Lisi does not get on the board
for Ravu.
Moto.
Ravu up.
Mookie going to try and set the
mark.
Mookie takes a toss.
That won't cut it.
Target still wide open.
Two-handed toss, made it halfway
down the course.
Ravu.
Just barely on the target, but
it will count.
Ravu now has the mark to beat.
Boo just short.
Ravu still in the lead.
Edgardo trying to improve the
mark set by his fellow tribemate
Dreamz.
He does not.
One good toss puts Moto back in
this.
>> Damn it.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man heads over
for Moto.
>> Come on, Yau-Man!
Whoo!
>> PROBST: A lot of target open
there, Yau-Man.
Yau-Man pulling an Evel Knievel,
going way back.
And it works!
Yau-Man sets the new mark to
beat.
>> From the free throw line.
>> Michael Jordan!
>> Look at that muscle!
>> PROBST: Alex is Ravu's last
hope in this round.
Got to get inside the mark set
by Yau-Man.
This round is worth two points.
Moto leads one point-zero.
If Alex doesn't beat Yau-Man's
mark, Earl won't have to go in
this round, either.
Alex ricochets off two targets,
doesn't hit either one.
Moto wins the second round.
Moving on to the last round, bow
and arrow.
Here's where we stand.
Moto leads three-zip.
This round is worth three
points.
If Ravu wins this round and we
are tied, we will go to sudden
death.
Sudden death will be with the
bow and arrow, one shooter, one
arrow, one winner.
Ravu, you're up.
Lisi not on the board for Ravu.
Moto.
Stacy wide to the right.
Ravu, you're up.
Mookie would like to set a nice,
tough mark for Moto to beat.
And he does not.
The target is still wide open.
Moto.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Michelle just barely
on the target.
Ravu, you're up.
Ravu now has the mark to beat.
Boo up for Moto.
Ravu still in the lead.
Alex up for Ravu.
That won't cut it.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Yau-Man.
What kind of move will he have
with the bow and arrow?
Yau-Man, what are you possibly
looking for?
>> The straightest possible
arrow.
>> Come on, Yau!
>> PROBST: Yau-Man once again
brings his own style.
Yau-Man takes the lead for Moto.
It comes down to Edgardo for
Ravu.
Ravu needs to win this round to
force a tie.
Otherwise Moto wins immunity,
and Earl will not have to
participate in this challenge at
all.
>> PROBST: Moto wins immunity!
Moto, congratulations.
The new Moto tribe has not lost
immunity.
Ravu, once again, you have a
date with me at tribal council.
One of the five of you going
home.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> How do we do so horrible?
We did bad.
>> I'm done with the losers.
These guys can't pull it
together.
Can I just say loser?
Loo-oo-ser.
I'm surrounded by losers.
You know what's going on?
That they know that they suck.
And when you know you suck, you
suck.
Dude, I'm telling you, this
whole tribe is a sinking ship.
There was no reason for you guys
to lose today.
Quite frankly, I don't see you
guys winning the next reward
challenge, and that means I get
to go to Exile Island again.
I'm not trying to buy real
estate, dude, you know what I'm
saying?
>> I understand.
>> I just really feel like my
time is up, and before I drive
myself crazy, I'd rather just
let you guys know how I'm
feeling, you know?
>> I just don't understand.
>> Lisi decided today that she
wants to be the next one to go.
She says she's had the
experience she wants to have,
and is grateful that Ed and I
kept her safe for as long as we
did, and it's just done, so she
told us she wants to go next.
>> I don't know what went awry,
you know?
>> I ran the gamut in this game,
I've been rich, I've been poor,
I've been in exile.
What more have I got to do?
I'm going to cry.
Oh!
>> The fact that Lisi wants to
quit pissed me off because I
could probably use her in the
future, because she's a solid
vote, but hey, I try not to
judge people in life.
I'm not going to judge Lisi now.
>> I knew if I talked to you
guys, you guys probably wouldn't
have voted me off, you know?
And that to me is like... I
don't know.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, and it's something
that's going to be treasured
forever.
We're going to be friends, end
of story, no more crying.
Sometimes you have to know when
it's time to go.
And I just kind of feel like
it's the end of the game for me.
I've gotten further than I ever
thought I would get, and I just
don't see the need to push
myself any further.
I'm done like a Thanksgiving day
turkey, man-- I'm done.
But it's cool, it's cool.
Well, we have tribal council
tonight, and pretty much, Lisi's
gone.
She's just laying there like
she's a sad puppy, so it's time
for her to go.
Getting rid of her is a dream
come true for me.
I don't know how the rest of the
boys feel about it, but I'm so
happy.
At tribal council, I might not
even be paying attention,
Jeff will be talking, and I'll
just get up and start taking
votes myself.
>> Going into tribal council,
I'm not going to take my bags.
I'm just going to tribal council
because I got plans on coming
back.
>> What would happen if we kept
on going?
>> I don't know.
What do you want me to say?
>> Look, I'm just thinking a
little bit more, that's all.
I'm having second thoughts.
All I can say is I was sitting
here thinking, and I was
thinking some more, and that's
why I pulled you guys over.
>> Okay, Lisi changed her mind
again.
I mean, she's gone back and
forth, like, three times.
So, I mean, I throw my hands up
in despair as if to say, "What
the hell?"
>> Okay, I'm looking at all
options.
Help me out here, guys.
Hello!
Alex and Edgardo, they know me.
The three of us are probably the
tightest three people in this
game.
And we've all had moments where
we've been at the brink, and
then something has pushed us
away or... but we've just kept
on playing.
>> Tonight we have to go to
tribal council and vote somebody
out.
So I mean, is it Lisi or Dreamz?
We haven't decided who's going
to be the target.
And that worries me a little
bit, but, I mean, you have to do
what you have to do.
>> In my eyes, Dreamz should be
the next one to go tonight.
I would vote for him, Alex would
vote for him, Edgardo would vote
for him.
So that's three votes.
Mookie's going to vote for me,
and Dreamz will vote for me as
well.
So Dreamz is going to end up
coming out of this.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the first member of our jury.
Rocky, voted out at the last
tribal council.
I'll remind you, the jury is
here merely to observe, listen
in, gather information to help
make a very big decision.
Since this new tribe formed,
you've lost four out of five
challenges.
Lisi, what's missing in this
tribe?
>> Well, there seems to be a lot
of individualism happening here.
The group cannot come together
as a cohesive force, and that's
how you see the other tribe
winning.
>> PROBST: You've had an
emotional ride.
>> Yeah, you could say that
again.
I mean, I've run the gamut in
this game.
I've been rich, I've been poor,
I've been in exile.
I've been all over the board.
So yeah, I've played this game.
There's no question about that.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, what are you
basing your vote on tonight?
>> You want me to be honest?
I think Lisi wants to go home
because she's not winning like
she was at the old Moto.
She gives up easily.
It's not hard to see that, Jeff.
>> I've seen you give up in the
middle of a challenge.
>> You've never see me give up.
>> Okay.
>> In your life you'll never see
me give up.
I can't give up.
It's not in me.
It can't be in me.
>> I've seen you not pull
through when it was time to,
like, pull through, like to
bring out the stuff from
underneath you.
>> When?
>> I saw you... okay, I can't
even do this, man.
>> Like I said, Jeff, I think
she wants to go home, and they
call me a genie in the bottle,
because I grant wishes.
>> PROBST: So Lisi, what is the
status of your will, your
desire?
>> It's, quite frankly, wavering
from minute to minute.
Sometimes I feel like there's
hope and sometimes I feel like
we're doomed.
>> PROBST: Edgardo, how do you
go and trust somebody who's been
so vocal about their uncertainty
in this game?
>> Well, based on the talks that
I have with Lisi, Lisi and I
don't have anything to hide from
each other.
She's told me everything.
I mean, winning a lot, then
losing a lot, then being on
Exile Island has affected the
way she's viewing the game.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, yes or no,
has your will dipped?
>> I'm glad you asked that.
My will is so opposite of hers.
Because I will fight.
You get what I'm saying, Jeff?
If I die, resuscitate me at the
finish line, you know what I
mean?
The warriors that I fight with,
we don't think we lose because
we suck.
So our spirit don't go down.
Her spirit goes down.
>> PROBST: So, Lisi, do you want
to be here?
>> Can't I catch a break?
I mean, there are times where
you're just not up to it.
I'm just being honest.
>> Well, I'm sorry, Jeff, I
really didn't get the answer to
that question, do she want to be
here.
She kind of moved around it, and
I didn't understand it at all.
Can you ask her again?
>> PROBST: You just did.
>> What?
>> Do you want to be here?
>> Okay...
>> It's a yes or no question,
Lis.
Do you want to be here, Alex?
>> Yes.
>> Do you want to be here,
Edgardo?
>> You know it.
>> Do you want to be here,
Mookie?
See how simple their answers
were?
>> Okay, that's fine.
>> They didn't give me a
shalingua... shiquare...
>> PROBST: Soliloquy?
>> Yeah.
They didn't give me one of
those.
>> All right, so I'm at fault
for being honest and saying
I have to think for a minute, I
have to just chill?
>> Jeff, I'm ready to vote.
>> PROBST: So Lisi, because we
have a vote about to happen,
what would you advise your tribe
to do?
>> Just give me a chance.
I mean, Edgardo and Alex know
me.
Dreamz, whether he wants to
admit that he knows me or not is
another story.
>> It's not that.
>> He's seen me around.
Okay, now I'm talking, okay, now
I'm talking!
So, you know, he's seen me
around, and he can judge my
actions, what have you.
Just give me a chance.
Just let me see what happens.
>> PROBST: Okay, let's get to
the vote.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, you would present it to
me before I read the votes.
It is time to vote.
Mookie, you're up.
>> I've been waiting to do this
for a long time.
>> You're a grown man.
Consider a name change.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Lisi.
Dreamz.
One vote Lisi, one vote Dreamz.
Lisi.
Two votes Lisi, one vote Dreamz.
Eighth person voted out, and the
second member of our jury, Lisi.
You need to bring me your torch.
Lisi, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, if there is one truth in
this game, it is you have to
want to win in order to make it
to the end.
Obviously you didn't feel Lisi
had that desire.
Good news is the four of you
remaining all say that you do.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
A mysterious tree mail...
>> "Gather your personal
belongings and paddle to Exile
Island immediately."
>> PROBST: ...shakes things up.
>> We've living on Exile Island?
>> PROBST: And a shocking twist
changes everything.
>> Oh, my god!
>> What the hell?
>> This is so messed up!
>> Oh, my god.
We're going to die.
>> You can sit there and say
whatever, but I know who I am.
It's not a matter of will.
When the ship is sinking, you
get off the ship.
Another thing, Ravu, you guys
are never going to get it
together.
You guys are losers, over and
over and over again.
There's nothing I could say,
other than try to hold on to
yourselves, because together
you're nothing.