>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, Dreamz had to decide
between two alliances: the four
horsemen or Earl, Yau-Man, and
Cassandra.
>> I can never tell how the game
is going to go, so I'm going to
just see how it plays out.
>> PROBST: First, Dreamz warned
Alex that he was on the chopping
block.
>> Alex, your name's going to
come up tomorrow.
>> PROBST: But Earl caught
Dreamz red handed.
>> You know I heard what y'all
was saying, right?
>> PROBST: Feeling the pressure
from Earl's alliance, Dreamz
dropped a bomb about the four
horsemen.
>> Mookie's got an immunity
idol.
>> There are two hidden immunity
idols.
The one in the Moto camp was dug
up by me.
>> PROBST: In their first
individual immunity challenge...
Yau-Man looks like he could go
all day.
...Yau-Man obliterated the
competition.
Boo is out of the challenge.
Yau-Man wins first individual
immunity.
Before tribal council....
>> Mookie wants to get rid of
Earl first.
Are you in?
>> PROBST: ...Alex tried to
recruit Stacy to join the four
horsemen...
>> I'm just hot.
I'm really agitated.
>> She was like, "I'm just
tired.
I'm just hot right now."
>> That means that she's not in,
dude.
>> PROBST: ...which put Alex at
risk.
>> I can save Alex by giving him
the immunity idol, but this
early in the game to use the
immunity idol is kind of a
disadvantage.
>> PROBST: Mookie reluctantly
passed his hidden immunity idol
to Alex in order to save him.
>> It's going to work, Mook.
It's going to work.
>> PROBST: And together, they
targeted Cassandra.
>> This is an all-or-nothing
move.
If it works out, it'll probably
be one of the best moves ever.
>> Mookie gave Alex the idol.
>> PROBST: Dreamz let his new
alliance know of the four
horsemen's plan.
>> He gave it to him?
>> I promise.
>> Listen-- Mookie, Mookie.
Mookie gave the idol to Alex, so
we're going to vote Mookie just
to catch them off guard.
>> Why don't we vote off
Edgardo?
>> PROBST: But unwilling to
fully trust Dreamz, the vote
switched to Edgardo.
>> If we hit them with Edgardo,
that hits them from the left
side.
>> Yeah, I've thought about it.
>> PROBST: And at tribal
council, Alex confidently played
Mookie's idol.
Alex is immune from tonight's
vote.
Alex, Mookie, and Edgardo were
certain their plan was working,
but when the votes were
revealed...
Tenth person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury...
...the rug was pulled out from
under them, and Edgardo was
voted out.
Edgardo, the tribe has spoken.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Yeah.
>> I thought Dreamz would be
more on par with the four
horsemen alliance, but I guess
not.
He's the one that turned and
back-stabbed us.
I mean, it hurts.
>> Everybody made a pact to vote
out Mookie, and then all of a
sudden they switched to Edgardo.
So I was the only one who voted
Mookie.
At first I felt like they didn't
trust me, but then they came to
me and they let me know that
they just changed it just in
case Mookie pulled out the
immunity idol.
And I was comfortable after
that.
>> That was brilliant.
Now the power is pretty much on
our side, and I feel good.
There ain't no more secrets now.
We're actually six strong, and
there's two people just waiting
on death row.
( theme song playing )
>> ...come over and say
something.
>> Like "Hey, guys, you know,
like, it's a game."
>> A true traitor.
>> Why are y'all not hanging out
no more?
>> Why do you think?
>> I'm still hanging out.
>> We all got outwitted?
What are you talking about?
>> We all got outsmarted last
night.
>> Dude, you turned on us.
>> No, I didn't turn on y'all.
>> How do you figure?
>> I didn't turn on y'all.
>> There were three votes for
Cassandra.
>> No, I didn't turn on y'all.
That's not even in me.
>> Why didn't you go with
Cassandra anyway?
>> Why didn't I go with
>> Yeah, that would have been a
4-4 split.
>> It would have been 4-4, and
that was the end of it.
We said Cassandra, and that was
it.
>> That was the end of it.
As soon as you voted for
Edgardo, that was the end of us.
>> What?
>> Or you voted for me?
>> Who'd you vote for, Mookie or
Edgardo?
>> I voted Mookie.
I didn't throw Mookie's random
name out randomly and turn on
y'all.
But I knew once they had us
gone, it's me trying to go with
them.
It's not me turning on y'all
ever, ever.
I walked over to Mookie and Alex
and said, "I guess we just got
outplayed," because I want them
to think that it wasn't my fault
that it happened.
I pretty much told them a story
about me not knowing about what
was going on.
I didn't turn.
>> That's the only thing that
was upsetting to me.
If I get jacked, I get jacked.
But to be turned on, I was like,
"Man, I can't believe that guy
turned on me."
>> I didn't go, "Oh, yeah, Alex
got the immunity idol, don't
vote for him; vote for Edgardo."
>> Is there a way out of this
right now?
>> One of y'all win the
challenge.
All y'all can do now is win
challenges.
As fast as I'm trying to get
them out of here, I still want
to be their friends, because I'm
going to need their vote in the
future if I one of the final
two.
I got a headache and everything
at tribal council.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
For today's challenge, you're
going to be randomly divided
into two teams.
One person from each team will
be on a platform.
You will be launching balls out
into the field, where your
teammates will run, slide, or
dive in the mud, attempting to
catch the ball using a catch
basket.
Each time you catch a ball, you
score a point.
It doesn't matter what color
ball you catch.
You catch a ball, you score a
point.
First team to five wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Some items to get you
nice and clean.
Trust me, all eight of you need
this desperately.
You will not take this back to
camp to get clean, though.
You will take this basket.
You will board a seaplane.
The seaplane will fly you to a
luxury spa resort.
>> Oh, God.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: When you arrive,
you'll take a shower, put this
Olay ribbons body wash to use.
You'll then spend the night, get
a good night's sleep in a bed,
return to camp in the morning.
In addition, the winning team
will send one person from the
losing team to Exile Island.
The person who goes to Exile
will find a new clue to the
location of the hidden immunity
idol, which has been rehidden
since Alex played it at the last
tribal council.
All right, we're going to
randomly draw for teams, and
we'll get started.
Here we go.
For the orange team, it is
Yau-Man launching balls to Boo,
Cassandra, and Mookie.
For the green team, launching
the balls is Stacy.
Out in the field, it is Dreamz,
Earl, and Alex.
Let's get this challenge
started.
Three, two, one, fire.
Yau-Man launches deep, nobody
going to get it.
Stacy waiting.
She launches.
Everybody going for it.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Earl has it, and he
loses it-- no points.
>> I didn't know they bounced
like that.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
launch.
Boo scores for orange!
Mookie steals it for the orange
team.
>> Sorry, sorry.
>> PROBST: Quickly, orange leads
two-zip.
Three, two, one, fire.
Alex makes a diving attempt but
cannot hold on to it.
>> Good try.
>> PROBST: What did I miss?
>> Choke hold.
>> PROBST: This is up to you
guys to figure out how physical
you want to get.
Ready, aim, fire.
Yau-Man goes short for Boo.
Stacy high and deep.
Dreamz has a shot.
Dreamz connects for green!
Orange leads now 2-1.
Three, two, one, fire.
Stacy launches deep for Dreamz.
Mookie almost steals it!
Yau-Man launches deep.
>> Ow!
Ow!
>> Are you all right?
>> PROBST: What happened, Boo?
>> Ow!
( Boo groaning )
>> PROBST: What happened, Boo?
>> I think it's my ACL or
something.
>> Take your time.
Take your time.
( Boo groaning )
>> PROBST: Let's bring medical
in.
( Boo groaning )
>> In the back?
>> Yeah, yeah, right in there.
>> Oh, man.
( knee popping )
>> Ooh!
>> Oh, man.
>> I can hear that.
>> I'm good.
I'm good.
Let's go.
Let's go!
>> PROBST: You want to keep
going?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: All right.
>> It was painful.
That's all.
It's gone.
The pain subsided.
>> PROBST: Boo going to keep
going.
Three, two, one, fire.
Boo battling for it and loses
it!
Dreamz scores for green!
>> Yau!
>> PROBST: We are now tied 2-2.
Three, two, one, fire.
Stacy's in the air.
Yau-Man goes short.
Mookie connects!
Orange back in the lead.
Three, two...
>> Earl, get physical!
>> I am physical.
It's about the placement of the
balls.
>> PROBST: Ready, aim, fire.
First ball in the air, Dreamz
going for it, and he has it!
Boo almost had it.
>> Come on, man!
>> PROBST: We are tied 3-3.
Three, two, one, fire.
Alex has a shot at it.
Yau-Man going way left to
Mookie.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Orange leads now 4-3.
We are at game point.
Orange scores one more point,
they're going to a spa.
>> Yau, patience.
Just watch the break.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
fire.
Yau-Man goes right back to the
same target.
Alex steals it for the green
team.
Stacy goes deep for Dreamz.
Boo with the good deflection,
does not score.
We are tied 4-4.
Next catch wins it.
Three, two, one, launch.
Boo has a shot at it, just
misses.
>> Dreamz!
>> PROBST: Dreamz has it.
Green scores!
Green wins reward!
Earl, Dreamz, Alex, and Stacy
going on a spa reward.
All right first big decision,
Alex, Stacy, Dreamz, and Earl,
you have to send one person to
Exile Island.
>> Boo.
>> He's been living the life of
luxury since he's been here, so
he has to go.
>> PROBST: Boo, head on out.
The boat will pick you up.
>> Good luck, Boo.
>> PROBST: Big reward.
>> Big, huge!
>> PROBST: Come grab your stuff.
Head on out this way.
The seaplane will pick you up.
>> Right now?
>> PROBST: You're going dirty,
just like this.
>> "The idol is back at your
very own beach.
It's close to a singular tree
and easy to reach."
It's not here.
It's not my beach.
That makes it a lot easier for
me here, because I don't want to
do anything.
I hurt my knee, and it's
painful.
I'm out of water right now.
I'm nearing heat exhaustion.
Man, I cannot be in the sun
anymore.
I'm going to die.
>> It's great.
The first thing I'm going to do
when I get to this reward is see
if I can wiggle my way back into
this alliance.
I mean, I'm certainly in a bad
position, and I feel like odds
are against me.
>> Bula-Bula!
>> Bula!
>> But, hey, I'm definitely
going to give it my all.
>> Hey, let's go ahead and get
sexy back.
We got the showers.
>> There's, like, so much dirt
in so many places, I don't know
what to do.
>> Warm water.
>> Oh, wow, this feels great.
>> I have mud under my arms.
How crazy is that?
Mud!
>> Time to Olay-- Olay, Olay.
Oh, my God, I'm clean again,
like human.
>> I don't know, Alex.
I think I'm getting my sexy
back.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Thank you.
>> Looks good, smells good.
>> Enjoy.
>> Getting the reward was good,
and it was definitely good for
morale.
>> I'm going to do the cheese
platter and that as well.
>> But it was extremely awkward
to have Alex there.
>> I mean, you've seen how I
play this game.
Whether I win or lose, I
congratulate the other team, and
I try to minimize, like, the
showboating.
>> Sometimes.
>> A lion is most dangerous when
he's wounded and backed up
against a wall.
That's how I feel, because I'm
clearly on the chopping block.
So if I can buy myself a couple
people off, that might give me
more time to try to maybe
infiltrate the alliance.
>> Yeah!
So can I ask you a question,
Earl?
>> Sure.
>> So what's the order, Mookie
and I?
>> That information probably
wouldn't be revealed, because
the game isn't over.
>> Fair enough.
>> Can't be stupid.
>> I'm assuming you want to go
second.
>> I think Mookie wants to go.
>> Sounds reasonable to me.
But I've come to terms with the
way I've played the game so far,
and I'm happy.
Obviously, I'm at a
disadvantage, but I don't care.
I'm not going down without a
fight, you know, and they the
better be prepared forward me to
bring it at this point.
>> Get out of our seats!
We're ready to get on!
>> So fresh and so clean.
>> We can smell you from here!
>> Clean, washed, pressed.
>> When the people came back
from the spa reward, they
smelled like apples and
strawberries.
>> Let me smell you!
Let me smell you!
>> I know, I smell good.
>> Yes, their trip was great,
but I just hate hearing it.
You're back to your standard of
living you're used to, dirt.
At this point, I'm already x'd
out of the equation of everyone,
but even though I seem like I'm
out of the game, I'm just
completely out, my heart is
still going, and my mind is
constantly just thinking.
I think Yau-Man found it.
>> The idol.
>> Yau-Man found it because he's
the only person that's ever at
camp.
>> Ever.
>> Always by the fire.
>> And he's always by the fire,
and he always has time, so he
has it.
When your back is against the
wall, you start being creative.
And I thought, "Hmm, the idol, I
wonder who really has the idol."
So I decided, "Well, Yau-Man's
fishing, the first time he's
ever been away from camp; I
might as well go check his bag
to see if there's anything in
there," just being curious.
Where's Yau-Man's bag?
Did he take it with him?
This is it right here?
Yup, he has it.
>> Are you serious?
>> Yeah, he's got it.
It's right here.
Look.
>> What can we do with that
information?
Do we blow up his spot?
>> We can do something with this
information.
Let's go think what is the most
damage we can cause.
>> I'm doing this because you
and me are the last two girls.
>> This is to a long and
prosperous game together.
>> Cheers.
>> That's why you don't hide the
immunity idol in your bag.
( laughter )
>> I hear somebody coming.
>> It's Yau-Man's best interest
not to align himself with us,
though, because we know he has
it.
Because there's no reason why he
would tell anybody yet, right?
>> There's nothing for his
position.
How are you going to convince
everyone that Yau-Man has the
idol?
>> Let's think about that.
>> Say, "I went in his bag.
He has the idol."
"You guys went fishing, I went
in his bag, he has the idol,
period."
>> He wears those pants to
tribal all the time.
"Yau-Man, do you have the idol?"
He's like, "No, I don't have the
idol."
"Pull your pants out and show
everyone here that you have the
idol if you're so confident."
>> Just blow up his spot at
tribal.
>> Right there, be like, "Throw
it up."
At tribal council, that's
like... if you blew him up on
the spot like that, and he had
it in his pocket, and then he
lied to everyone saying he
didn't have it...
>> They would vote with us.
>> Exactly.
>> God, it's going to be so
great!
Even if we get voted off, Mook,
it's going to feel so great!
That's going to feel so... ah!
That's going out swinging,
literally a blaze of glory.
>> Scarface.
>> Scarface style.
>> Two great brains working
together, strategizing, we're on
top of the world.
>> Ah, brilliant.
>> We devised this huge plan of
maybe we can bring up the idol
to everyone and surprise them at
tribal council, then people
won't be able to talk to each
other and people will be
paranoid; they don't know what
to do.
It's going to be an interesting
tribal council, let me tell you
that.
>> It is.
( laughter )
( twig breaks )
>> What?
>> Stacy and Cassandra are right
there.
>> We're screwed.
That's it.
They're going to tell Yau-Man.
>> There goes that plan.
>> Damn it, dude!
>> Right now the biggest thing
is we need to blow his spot up.
>> We blow up his spot before
tribal council.
>> We blow it up now.
>> We got to hurry up and go
there then, before they go.
Time to raise some hell.
>> Once I saw Stacy and
Cassandra listening to our
conversation, I came up with a
little idea that if we can get
back to Yau before them and kind
of give him an ultimatum, that
we can somehow use that
information against him in his
alliance.
>> I think they may be a little
paranoid, thinking we were
eavesdropping in on them.
>> Cassandra and I happened to
be sitting nearby where Mookie
and Alex were having a
conversation that they spoke
about a few things that we
didn't hear.
We heard, like, words here and
there.
So then they went running back
to camp.
>> Now, do you want to tell the
group yourself, or do you want
us to do it?
>> Why do I have the idol?
>> I thought you guys were
getting firewood.
>> No.
>> So what do you want to do,
Yau?
>> You guys do what you need to
do.
>> Okay, we will.
>> All right.
>> So we go to Yau-Man, and he
was shocked.
I definitely saw it in his eyes,
like, "Holy crap."
He's not going to be able to now
use the idol the way he wanted
to.
So that still makes him more of
a target than it did before.
It'll be interesting, won't it?
>> Earl is the only one who
knows I have the idol.
At this point, it doesn't change
any outcome, because my voting
bloc members, we already have
decided, we have the majority to
continue the sequence that we
are going to.
It changed somewhat for me,
personally, because having that
information that early put me at
risk.
So I will have to tell all my
voting bloc just straight out.
>> He went through your bag,
Yau-Man?
>> He went through my bag.
They're trying to threaten me,
basically.
He didn't say that.
He implies that, pretty much.
>> My heart is, like, hurting
right now.
Alex went through Yau-Man's
things, his bag, his pants, and
then threatened him.
>> He threatened you?
>> He threatened him and said,
"I know you have the immunity
idol."
>> He looked at me and said, "I
saw it in your pants.
What are you going to do about
it?"
>> Yau went and told everybody
that they went through
everybody's bags and they found
the idol.
>> To go through people's
personal stuff and then to try
to bully you?
>> Yeah.
>> People were pissed that they
went through Yau's personal
things, not about, "Okay, Yau
has the idol."
>> That's dirty.
That's dirty.
>> But it sucked to me just
because someone knew, because I
like keeping everything quiet in
general.
That's just... because too many
people knowing about things, bad
things happen.
>> Who went through your bag,
though?
>> I don't know who, but they
did, because I just checked.
My pants are all ruffled up, and
I usually fold it nicely.
>> Finding out that Yau-Man had
the immunity idol changed a
whole bunch of stuff, because
everybody with an immunity idol
is considered dangerous.
Me, Cassandra, and Stacy know
that.
Everybody else is going to be on
a whole different level.
It's going to change a whole
bunch of stuff.
>> You know what?
At least it caused them some
dissension.
That's what we wanted.
You know what I mean?
>> The worst thing that can
happen is either Alex or Mookie
wins the next immunity
challenge, and somehow they
manage to get Dreamz and Boo to
their side.
Then it will be a 4-4 split.
And if we lose that 4-4 split,
it may be downhill for me.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Boo returning
from Exile Island.
>> My tribe mates, my friends,
how y'all doing?
>> PROBST: First thing's first.
Yau-Man, I'll take back the
necklace.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
Today's challenge requires a
strong memory and a lot of
strategy.
You will each secretly select
your own block of three squares
on a grid.
They must line up either
horizontally, vertically, or
diagonally.
Then you're going to attempt to
knock out your opponents by
selecting coordinates and
bombing squares one by one.
The object of the game is to
knock out all of the squares of
your tribe mates.
The last person to still have a
square left on the grid wins
immunity, guaranteed a one-in-
seven shot at winning this game.
Losers go to tribal council
tonight.
Somebody will be going home.
Anything not clear?
We'll get your positions, and
we'll get started.
All right, Stacy has secretly
selected her block of three
squares, as has Yau-Man, Mookie,
Cassandra, Dreamz, Boo, Alex,
and Earl.
Okay, so you all know your own
spots.
You don't know anybody else's.
So this is a little bit of a
guess and a lot of memory.
Dreamz, you're up first.
Fire away.
>> D-3.
>> PROBST: D-3 is a hit.
Oddly enough, Dreamz hits
himself, while also hitting Earl
and Boo.
Cassandra.
>> C-3.
>> PROBST: That is a hit.
That is a hit on Yau-Man and
Cassandra.
Cassandra blew up one of her own
positions on the target.
Mookie.
>> Uh... E-4.
>> PROBST: E-4 is a hit.
Earl takes his second hit.
Earl, make a selection.
>> B-4.
>> PROBST: B-4 is a good hit.
Earl hits Alex, Mookie, and
Cassandra, who now has only one
square left.
Yau-Man, make your choice.
>> C-2.
>> PROBST: That is a hit.
Dreamz and Boo both take their
second hit, and Earl takes his
third hit.
Earl is out of the game.
Stacy.
>> B-1.
>> PROBST: B-1 is a hit.
Boo takes a hit, and Dreamz
takes a hit.
And with that selection, Stacy,
you've knocked both Boo and
Dreamz out.
Take a spot on the mat, guys.
Alex.
>> D-2.
>> PROBST: D-2 is a miss.
Cassandra, your choice.
>> Can I have A-4, please?
>> PROBST: Miss.
Mookie.
>> A-5.
>> PROBST: A-5 is a hit.
Cassandra takes her third hit.
Cassandra, you're now out of the
challenge.
Yau-Man, chance to do some
damage.
>> C-5.
>> PROBST: Mookie takes a hit
and Stacy takes a hit.
Mookie now with one square left.
Alex.
>> B-5.
>> PROBST: miss.
Stacy.
>> A-4.
>> PROBST: A-4 has already been
picked.
It's a miss.
Memory is starting to play an
important role in this game as
we get further and further into
it.
Mookie, your choice.
>> C-4.
>> PROBST: That is a hit.
Alex takes a hit.
Alex now has one square left.
Yau-Man, your choice.
>> A-3.
>> PROBST: That is a hit.
Mookie takes his third hit.
Mookie now joins Earl, Dreamz,
Cassandra, and Boo.
We are down to three people
left: Alex, Yau-Man, Stacy.
Alex has one square left,
Yau-Man and Stacy each with two.
Alex, a chance to do some
damage.
>> E-5.
>> PROBST: E-5 is a hit.
It is a hit on Yau-Man.
Yau-Man and Alex each with one
square left.
Stacy.
>> D-4.
>> PROBST: Stacy says D-4.
D-4 is a hit.
Everybody takes a hit.
A good strategic move, as Stacy
hits herself but, in the
process, takes out both Yau-Man
and Alex.
Stacy wins individual immunity.
( applause )
Stacy, safe at tonight's tribal
council.
Somebody going home.
Head on out.
>> I'm not going to share with
them... if you can imagine.
But eat that.
That'll help keep your energy
up.
I'm definitely up against the
wall, right?
I don't have very many moves
left, but I'm just not... I'm
not going to go down without a
fight.
I'm don't think I'm going to go
that quietly, just so you know.
>> And right now, we have
nothing to be but honest.
>> We have nothing to be but
honest, exactly.
So I'm going to be completely
honest.
>> Cause some hell.
>> Just cause some hell, man.
If I'm going down, I'm bringing
hell with me.
I'm a lawyer.
I know what it's like to
negotiate with people.
I know what it's like to use
information strategically, which
I've been doing all along.
You know, it's very clear.
Hey, Yau-Man can't be trusted.
So at tonight's tribal council,
I'm going to point it out as
"Hey, these are the people
you've aligned yourself with.
Draw your own conclusions."
>> Why take a chance?
>> Okay, okay, fine, all right,
whatever, we'll do...
>> Everybody give it some
thought.
>> Boo came back from Exile
Island, and he had one clue to
the hidden immunity idol, and I
think Boo somehow convinced
Cassandra or whoever that Alex
or Mookie may have found it
somehow.
They're afraid that Alex will
pull another one out.
So they're going to try and
spread the vote out.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> People want to do three votes
Mookie and three votes Alex, and
the reason for that was just you
never know what might pop up.
That will make it a tie at
tribal council.
So at that point, we can make a
choice.
We know that no magical idol has
been played, because there won't
be anything played, and we can
say okay, "It's going to be
Alex, that's who is going to
go," because that is who's going
to go.
>> Ready?
One, two, three.
>> I'm against doing a split
vote, but you know, I do what
makes people feel comfortable.
I'm not going to sit there and
say, "No, guys, we're going to
do this," because that would be
the wrong approach.
>> Tonight's tribal council,
Mookie and I are going out
swinging.
And if that doesn't work, I
think my best bet is to just try
to stay alive past this vote.
I've got one vote, and I better
make it count.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the jury: Rocky, Lisi, Michelle,
and Edgardo, voted out at the
last tribal council.
Let's start with the reward
challenge.
Alex, did you sense the game
shift at all?
There were a lot of physical
match-ups, a lot of people
yelling at each other.
>> I don't know if it changed
the game, but it definitely
revealed something about the way
people are willing to play
games, you know, if they're more
likely to rub mud in someone's
eyes or trip somebody.
And as Dreamz pointed out last
tribal council, the rats and the
snakes came out of the woodwork.
>> PROBST: Mookie, what did you
notice from that challenge?
>> I think, to some extent, we
respect each other.
But then, when it comes down to
the game and how are you going
to win, it's a little different.
I mean, there's two sides to the
story there.
>> PROBST: Tell me about the
other side.
>> There are alliances, and one
alliance was completely
destroyed at the last tribal
council, maybe some back
stabbing and maybe some
trickiness on the other
alliance's part.
But at that point, you feel
yourself just being an outsider
to an alliance.
>> PROBST: So, Mookie, what do
you do?
>> You know, Alex and I, we
realized our backs are against
the wall with no way out.
You know, we've come up with
some kind of way we can possibly
get out, and that was through an
immunity idol that we found in
one of the... in Yau-Man's bag.
>> PROBST: Hold on, you found an
immunity idol in Yau-Man's bag.
>> Correct.
>> PROBST: Found it?
>> Well, it was in his bag,
yeah.
>> PROBST: This is coming on the
heels of Alex saying the snakes
and the rats came out.
That's about as snaky-ratty as
it gets, going through
somebody's personal belongings.
Yau-Man, is that fair-- that "If
you're going something in your
bag and leave, you better know I
might look through it"?
>> Well, the expectation is
there's some privacy, but on the
other hand, you know, it's a
desperation move, and besides,
it won't affect the outcome of
the game for the next few
rounds.
>> PROBST: Well, that's a bold
statement.
It won't affect the game for the
next few rounds?
>> Couple rounds at least.
I may have to change my strategy
a little bit, if I, you know,
intend to use it at some point.
>> PROBST: Earl, what was the
reaction when this all went
down?
>> I was pissed.
Like, for one thing, I can say
that this tribe, no one's going
through anybody's stuff.
That just hasn't been going on.
So when I heard that, you know,
I was pissed off.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, how big an
issue is trust?-- because it's
hard to know who has been lying
all along.
>> My take on this is if they're
both on the chopping block,
after they're gone, it's still
going to be six of us left.
So we're going to split up too.
So I'm trying to find out where
I stand.
>> PROBST: Alex, are there
people coasting in this game
that are threats and aren't seen
as threats?
>> Yeah.
And at this point, if Mookie and
I are gone, and there are six
people left, and they have to
look at each other-- so whatever
they did to get to that top six
is going to come back and bite
them in the ass.
Karma has a funny way of working
in this game, Jeff, and it's
pretty immediate.
You know, whatever will be will
be, but word to the wise:
remember past actions, because
they foretell the future.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Based on tonight's tribal
council, we know there is
another hidden immunity idol in
play.
Whoever has it, if you need to
use it tonight, you would
present it to me before I read
the votes.
Stacy, you have individual
immunity.
Are you going hold on to it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Stacy.
Everybody else is fair game.
Time to vote.
Earl, you're up.
>> Nothing personal.
Someone needs to go.
>> Just trying to stay in this
another day, buddy.
Good luck.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If you have the hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now is the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
First vote: Alex.
Alex.
Two votes Alex.
Mookie.
Boo.
One vote Boo.
Mookie.
That's two votes Mookie, two
votes Alex, one vote Boo.
Mookie.
That's three votes Mookie.
Alex.
We're tied.
Three votes Mookie, three votes
Alex, one vote left.
Eleventh person voted out and
the fifth member of our jury,
Mookie.
You need to bring me your torch.
Mookie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Well, based on what I
heard tonight, it sounds like
there's one very strong group of
six and Alex, which means Alex
is either odd man out or
suddenly very valuable.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, Alex goes undercover.
>> I'm trying to make sure I'm
not seen or heard, kind of like
a ninja right now.
>> PROBST: Boo annoys everyone.
>> He talks more than the girls
talk.
>> Y'all know what I was
thinking.
I was like, "Would you shut up?
Why don't you stop saying stupid
stuff?"
>> PROBST: And the reward
challenge gets primal.
This is a free-for-all.
>> You know, I'm pretty relieved
that I'm out of the game, but at
the same time, it would have
been nice to still be in the
game had the alliances stayed
put for me.
And I wish I could be back
there, raising hell, making
everyone's lives miserable, as
miserable as my life has been
here.
It's kind of like grass is green
on the other side.
You know, it's unfortunate that
I'm out of the game, but it was
a great experience, and I
wouldn't take it back for
anything.