>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
On a remote island off the coast
of Fiji, 19 Americans were
marooned with no instructions.
>> We don't have a pot, we don't
have water, we don't have
anything, and none of us have a
clue what's going on.
>> Come on, we've got visitors!
>> PROBST: Then a message from
above quickly changed
everything.
>> "Welcome, survivors.
Construct the best possible
living area you can."
>> Holy cow, man!
>> All right!
>> PROBST: With an unprecedented
abundance of supplies...
>> Let's rock and roll.
>> PROBST: ...the castaways
begin to build the most
elaborate camp in Survivor
history.
>> The kitchen's going to be
right there.
>> PROBST: Sylvia the architect
spearheaded the construction
effort.
>> Hey, I notice nobody's
working on the kitchen.
We need a crew for the kitchen
or else it won't be done until
tomorrow.
>> I do get the sense that
Sylvia's trying to dominate.
You're going to upset the wagon
by doing that.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Sylvia's leadership
earned her the right to divide
the tribes.
Moto, you are green.
Ravu, you are orange.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> PROBST: Then Sylvia learned
she had immunity, but would be
banished to Exile Island.
You will rejoin this game by
joining the tribe that does lose
a member.
Exile Island awaits.
The stage was set for a high-
stakes challenge.
In addition to immunity, the
winning tribe gets to stay on
the beach that all 19 of you put
blood, sweat, and tears into
building.
Losers will go to a new beach
where you will find one pot and
one machete, and that's it.
Go!
During the challenge...
Jessica still working on the
pieces.
...Jessica slowed Ravu down.
Moto has their knife!
And Moto came out ahead.
Moto wins immunity and reward!
Ravu, here's a map to your new
beach.
Not much waiting for you.
On Exile Island...
>> "Here you won't find the idol
you crave."
>> PROBST: Sylvia discovered
that the hidden idol was back at
her tribe camp.
>> Now I have to figure out a
time when I can search for it
without prying eyes.
>> We're home!
>> PROBST: And Ravu landed on a
new beach.
>> We've got a double whammy.
We have to start over, a new
shelter, but now we've got to
figure out a team member to
lose.
>> PROBST: And at tribal
council...
First person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji, Jessica.
...the tribe singled out Jessica
as the weak link.
Jessica, the tribe has spoken.
18 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> The leaves have water on
them.
Water!
>> Tree licking good.
>> This is the weirdest thing
I've ever done.
But it's good.
I think I'm going to grab a
couple of more.
>> It's like tree hugging.
>> Let's go.
>> So it's day four on the
island, and we're dehydrated.
We're so desperate for water
that we found that there's
trickle bits of water on leaves,
and so just licking the leaves
and getting as much water as
possible, we thought that would
be a good idea.
>> Oh, no!
>> Seriously, just lick some
leaves, man.
The palms are better.
>> I've never... have you ever
licked a leaf before?
>> We need to survive.
It's hard to even think when
you're dying of starvation and
thirst.
Thirst before anything.
>> You missed one.
>> It's just a little bit of
dirt.
>> We're all just dehydrated.
It makes you delirious.
>> Lick it.
>> So good.
>> How did you guys sleep?
>> I slept really well last
night.
The pillows really make a
difference.
It's ridiculous.
>> We are very fortunate to be
living the way that we're
living.
Yesterday we did win one hell of
a reward.
( scat singing )
♪ We are in an island. ♪
( laughter )
>> We do have a really plush
couch, beautiful pillows that we
could sleep on.
There's two hammocks.
You know, we have silverware,
plates.
We're all more than happy.
We're all sitting around
thinking the same thing-- this
game is so vicious, it's
delicious.
I just killed an ant with a
hammer.
( laughing )
What a great death.
>> Yeah, man.
It's rough out here.
Belly full of salted rice, fresh
mangoes, lemonade.
>> There's some more rice in
here.
>> Of course, we made it
ourselves.
The fat of the land.
( farting sound )
>> Oh, my god!
Boo!
Oh, for the love of Pete.
>> That's air.
It's not like a sea urchin.
>> Still!
>> We're already full.
You know, this is going to be
the first Survivor where you
actually gain weight when you
come.
>> We have a lot to do over
there.
A nice, long, groove.
See, that's what we need.
>> Come on!
>> It's tiring.
It's very tiring.
>> It is.
>> It's going to take a long
time to do.
Do you want to take a break?
>> Go, go, go, go, go.
>> Right now, Ravu is in pretty
bad shape.
We've got heart for days, but
heart doesn't do any good when
you're as thirsty and hungry as
we are.
We rub sticks and we rub more
sticks.
Rubbing sticks is great if you
have 30 people who are all
hydrated and have energy.
When you have eight people who
are tired as hell and who have
no water in their system, it
burns you out pretty fast.
>> So since we did not get any
fire yet and weren't able to
boil water, the plan here is to
fill up as many canisters as we
can with coconut water.
With a good knife, it takes
about a minute to crack open a
coconut.
With a bad knife it takes, like,
three, four, minutes.
I mean, that really takes a lot
more energy.
>> I think I can get one open in
one minute.
What's that, 30 seconds?
>> Ooh!
A little cocky, are we, buddy?
I didn't know we had a
competition.
>> Let's get the stopwatch out.
>> Trying to take your title,
there.
>> They are completely full.
>> Are you kidding me?
Nothing!
>> Today, what's going on is
basically everyone's beat.
Nobody really has the energy to
chop anything open or run
around, so you, like, chop up
five coconuts, take a nap for an
hour.
I'm telling you, right now,
nobody has a clue.
We're walking around into the
rocks and the trees, guy.
Half of us can't even stand up
for more than, like, an hour and
a half, I'm telling you.
I just... you know, I've never
experienced dehydration like
this so much.
You guys want this, or what?
>> Rocky, just swallow it.
>> Yeah?
I was eating clams off the
ground.
I don't do that!
I eat clams, too.
I don't eat them off the ground.
Huh?
No!
It's crazy!
We're starving here, bro!
>> On the stick?
>> On the sign.
>> Man, you'd better get some
water into that.
>> Boo caught something in his
eye, and his eye's red.
He's got an obvious indentation
in his eye.
Just blink with your eye as I'm
pouring it in.
Try to go as long as you can.
Just blink.
Just keep it, keep it.
It's going to be bad.
It's going to be annoying.
Just keep it.
All right.
>> Look how he dropped that ax
so close to his leg.
>> Oh, my god, Boo, be careful.
>> Oops.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Oh, my god, Boo, how did it
happen?
>> Hang on.
>> I just barely finished
helping him with the eye
situation, and the next thing
you know, he takes an ax, and
literally the ax went through
the finger and right down to the
knee.
>> Quit worrying about my
injury.
>> We aren't worrying about your
>> We have other stuff we need
to do.
>> Like what?
>> I will tell y'all when I
think I need some help.
>> It's too late then, Boo.
Boo is very stubborn.
He's a real hazard to himself.
I can see it happening where we
don't have to vote nobody out
sooner or later.
For real, he has one leg, one
hand, and one eye.
He really ain't no good to us
now.
What can we do?
We've got to think about that
kind of stuff.
That's the kind of stuff I'll be
thinking about, you know what
I'm saying?
Everybody knows it.
Everybody is predicting it.
Boo will hurt himself out of the
game.
>> Darn it, Boo!
>> Oh, my god.
>> Had to happen to me.
>> Sylvia.
>> Is she here?
>> Yeah.
Yeah, there she is.
Come on, you guys.
>> Hey, Anthony!
What are you guys called again?
>> Ravu.
>> Ravu!
I knew it was going to be good.
Did you guys make a home?
>> Huh?
>> Did you make a home or are
you waiting for me?
>> We waited for you.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Oh, my god, it was horrible.
Hi!
I was... I was hoping... I was
hoping I would be on your team.
>> Welcome home!
When Sylvia came back from Exile
Island, everybody was excited.
But when I went up to greet her,
I had only one thing in my mind,
and that was to see if she found
the immunity idol.
So when I was giving her a hug I
was actually quite nasty.
I looked over her shoulder and
opened up her shoulder bag and
did a little quick search, and I
didn't find anything.
>> Oh, my god!
>> That was my first thought in
mind-- "When I'm hugging her,
I'm going to feel her up and see
if the idol is there."
>> I made fire for the first
time in my life.
There's no flint here?
>> No, we had no fire here.
>> We've got nothing.
>> We don't have water.
>> So when I got here and they
told me they had no fire and no
water at all, you know, you're
just kind of like, "We're stuck
in a really bad situation."
So how many canteens do we have
filled yet?
>> None.
>> We're just starting the
process.
Okay.
Isn't that awesome?
>> Here.
I'll try it, Erica.
Okay, so...
>> You need to give it a good
whack.
Here, over the... so you drip...
>> Hey, it ain't working for me,
guys.
>> Harder.
Just hit hard.
>> I am!
I feel like at this point I'm a
bit extraneous.
I'm a bit like... because I
missed the whole day with them,
and they've got the whole rhythm
going, so I feel like I'm coming
in and trying to help, but I'm
not...
>> Oh, man.
>> ... you know, part of the
core right now.
If the sun gets intense for long
enough, you might get something
there.
It looks like your left hand
could use a little support.
Could you?
Um...
>> Michelle.
>> Yeah.
>> I was not really excited for
Sylvia to come back.
I already didn't have great
feelings about her personality.
I personally think she's a
little bossy, and just likes to
push people around.
>> How about fishing along the
shore?
>> We can try it.
>> You know, if this is low
tide, we ought to go out and get
some oysters.
>> In many ways, Sylvia's the
outsider.
She kind of does rub people the
wrong way.
I mean, it's not so much that
she's a bad person.
It's just that she's... for lack
of a better word, she's bossy.
>> Yep.
If I throw the machete, are you
going to catch it?
>> There you go.
>> Being on Survivor is pretty
much a little bit easier than
being homeless.
Hey, watch out!
Look, I'm going to bring down a
family of them.
>> Oh, that was a good one,
buddy.
You got six out of that.
>> When I was first homeless, I
was about seven years old
because my momma started doing
drugs.
>> I wouldn't step on that one
for too much security.
>> Our momma was a crackhead.
And my brothers and sisters and
I decided all we got is each
other and ourselves.
And so we used to just get the
food out of the trash can that
people throw away.
It's very similar, having to go
out and get food, having to find
food.
And when you find food you ain't
going to be greedy and eat it
yourself because you're hungry,
because you know everybody else
is hungry, too.
>> That's beautiful.
That's a beautiful thing.
>> There's so much more, there
are so many more.
The more trees we find, the more
we run wild.
I know my teammates don't know
what it's like to suffer.
When I first got here, I was
like, "What are these people
doing here?"
I don't think they know what
it's like to struggle.
I think this is the most
struggle some people had that's
here, which is not really even a
struggle to me.
This is easier than being
homeless on the street.
I know people are going to be
jealous.
People sitting at home, they're
going to be jealous, because
we've got more food here than
they have in their refrigerator.
>> Oh, wow.
That would be sad.
>> Yeah, that would be really
sad.
>> This is more food that I've
got in my refrigerator.
>> I have a weight of
responsibility to last in this
game, because I do want to help
my family.
I'm in an amazing spot in my
life right now.
I'm going to help my family when
I get back.
>> Ahoy!
I am beyond starving.
I'm looking for anything, any
tree of life, anything.
>> Look on the ground, man.
>> Hey, this is something.
Are those nuts?
>> Mango, bro.
>> Yeah, it's a mango.
This is definitely the beginning
stages.
Can't eat them.
I'm going to go up here a little
bit more and see.
We went all the way up to the
top, around, nothing.
I went all the way up that way.
There's no other fruit here.
Nothing.
>> Oh, my god.
Pineapples.
There are so many of them.
Hey!
>> Oh, my god!
>> Pineapples.
This is ready.
>> Pineapple!
>> We're running around hungry
and stupid for the past few
days.
We've been looking over there.
>> Amazing!
>> Beautiful!
>> We've been trekking the whole
island, climbing mountains and
stuff, and right in front of us
has been, like, hundreds of
pineapples, sitting there.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Erica, you're the hero.
>> No way!
>> Oh, sweet!
>> Oh, my god!
>> We've got pineapple power for
the challenge tomorrow.
>> This is huge.
This is... now I'll be ready.
I'll be ready.
Wow, a miracle.
And she just stumbled on to it.
Me and Erica, we're getting
married now.
She just saved my life.
And I appreciate that.
That's a good woman.
>> I just want to smile.
I just want to smile.
>> Yo!
>> Hey!
>> What is that thing?
>> Tree mail?
>> Bring it here.
>> Is that fire?
>> We got mail.
>> No.
No fire, stupid.
He goes, "Fire?"
Yeah, I got fire right here,
buddy.
"Run, paddle, pull, think.
This one's anybody's game.
Teamwork and the will to win..."
>> We've got the will!
We've got the will!
>> That's right.
..."helps with food and saves
your flame."
>> Key word, "flame," baby.
We've got fire.
>> We've got flint.
We've got heart.
>> I am not going to have any
problems kicking butt today.
It's definitely all about
payback today.
I mean, we helped build that
shelter.
We wasted all of our fresh
energy on making that camp home.
So today is the day that we can
get back at them and we can make
them suffer a little bit.
>> Ow!
>> I want to win for many
reasons.
I'm the most vulnerable member
of the tribe right now, having
been an outsider, and I've
realized for a couple of days
now, of course, that the
immunity idol is here at camp.
But I haven't had the strength,
the energy, or really
opportunity to go look for it.
So there is no option for me to
lose.
Because I know the consequences.
>> I hope y'all feel that
nervousness coming on.
It's time.
It's go-home day.
It's go-home day for somebody.
Somebody got to go home today.
And we don't plan on it being
us.
It's go-home day, and we want to
stay on go-home day.
>> Y'all doing it, I'm going it.
It's definitely game on, and
we're pumped.
We're pumped in more ways than
they can imagine.
Our tribe has a distinct
advantage.
It's a huge advantage where
we've been fed, we've been
happy, we've been cracking up
laughing, we've been sleeping
well.
We're going to be calm.
We're going to be steady.
They're going to be nervous.
We don't want to lose, but we
know in our minds we're not
starting from the bottom
anymore.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Moto, getting your first look at
the new Ravu tribe.
Jessica voted out at the first
tribal council.
Sylvia has taken her spot.
First order of business.
Sylvia, your buff.
You're now official.
>> Finally.
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first.
Take back immunity.
Immunity, back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, each
tribe will paddle in a canoe out
and around your tribe flag.
On your way back, you must
collect four supply crates.
Each time you paddle over a
crate, one tribe member will
attach a long rope to the crate.
Once you're back to shore,
you'll pull the crates in and
carry them to your tribe mat.
When you have all four crates on
your mat, you'll untie them to
find six puzzle pole pieces and
a flag.
The first tribe to correctly
assemble their puzzle pole with
their flag and raise it wins the
challenge.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: A lot of fishing
gear.
>> Nice.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: Ravu, because you
still do not have fire, you're
still playing for fire in the
form of flint.
>> Let's get it, baby.
>> PROBST: Talk about making a
change.
It would be nice to have some
water, wouldn't it?
>> Yes, it would.
>> PROBST: And the most
important thing in this game,
immunity.
In addition, the winning tribe
will choose one member from the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island.
There is a lot at stake, winner
take all.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Give you a minute to
strategize, we'll get started.
Here we go.
Ravu looking for some revenge.
Moto looking to put them deeper
in the hole.
For reward and immunity,
survivors ready?
Go!
Got to go out past your flag and
then head back!
>> Row!
Row!
Dig deep, you guys!
>> All right, you guys, reverse
it, reverse it.
>> Start backpedaling.
>> Go backwards.
>> PROBST: Ravu makes the turn.
Moto makes the turn.
Both tribes dead even as they
pass their flag heading back.
Rain starting to come down.
Ravu right on line.
>> Say when, say when.
>> PROBST: Michelle clips in for
Ravu.
>> Push!
Push!
>> PROBST: Stacy clips in for
Moto.
>> Don't stop!
Don't stop!
>> Row!
>> PROBST: Ravu with a bit of a
lead.
Ravu clipped into their second
crate.
>> Go!
>> Push, push!
>> Stop, stop, stop!
>> Get it out of the boat!
>> PROBST: Moto's rope is
tangled.
They're losing time.
Ravu getting a big break.
>> Hurry!
Come on!
>> PROBST: Moto has their second
crate.
Michelle clips in for Ravu,
extending the lead.
>> Backpedal here.
Backpedal!
>> You guys, keep it going.
>> PROBST: Michelle has clipped
in the fourth and final crate
for Ravu.
They're heading back to shore.
>> Let's go!
>> Stacy clips in with the third
crate for Moto
>> Untangle that rope.
Come on, let's go!
>> PROBST: Moto clipping into
their fourth crate.
They're heading to shore.
It's going to come down to
strength now.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Which tribe can get
their crates in more quickly?
Ravu working together very well.
Still with the lead.
Ravu, got to get that fourth
crate up there.
Keep moving!
Go, start untying!
Ravu untying their crates.
Moto back with their third
crate.
The guys trying to get that
fourth crate back quickly.
Go, Moto!
Start untying!
>> Let's go!
Put it together now!
>> PROBST: Which tribe works
together well here will win this
challenge.
>> I have the bottom piece.
>> It's not fitting.
>> That was it!
>> PROBST: Erica certain she's
right.
Nobody's listening.
>> Everybody calm down.
>> PROBST: Moto very close.
>> That's it, turn it.
Put it in, put it in!
>> PROBST: Moto thinks they have
it.
>> Go, go, go!
>> Everybody!
>> One, two, three!
>> PROBST: Moto wins the
challenge!
>> PROBST: Moto, once again,
you're safe from tribal council,
and you'll be taking back a lot
of fishing gear.
Ravu, more bad news for you.
Somebody's going to be going to
Exile Island.
The only saving grace is that
whoever Moto chooses will be
safe from tribal council
tonight.
Moto, give me your decision.
>> It's Earl.
>> PROBST: Okay, Earl.
Boat's waiting for you.
You will get another clue to the
whereabouts of a hidden immunity
idol.
Watch out for the sea snakes.
>> I'll eat them.
>> PROBST: Ravu, tonight you
lose another member to tribal
council.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
>> "Here you won't find the idol
you crave.
Search back at your camp if you
hope to be saved."
Clue number two:
"To search with success you must
become centered under the
highest point upon which you
have entered."
Back at the camp where I just
left?
Wow!
To find out that the idol was
back at camp was very shocking.
But it doesn't really matter
that Sylvia has that first clue,
because as of tonight, she most
likely will be gone.
Exile is an upgrade from how we
were living.
For one, I have fire.
But at the same time, I'm not
involved on what's going on at
the camp.
There's a freaking snake.
The highly poisonous sea snake.
Can't take that chance.
That same one.
It's like Saving Private Ryan.
If you let that one go, it might
come back and get you later.
Sorry, buddy.
I really don't like killing
animals.
Snakes are misunderstood.
But we have an understanding
now.
>> That one was a tough loss,
guys.
Just wait till the challenges
when there aren't no puzzles.
We'll kill everybody, you know
what I mean?
>> I love you.
>> It's the puzzles that kick
our ass every time, bro, every
time.
>> Here we are, we bust our
asses today, and what do we got?
Nothing.
Empty-handed.
You know, we can't even win with
the sun.
And now we've got to go to
tribal council again.
And that's just frustrating.
I'm just mad.
I'm mad and a whole lot tired,
and it's only day six.
It's only day six!
I just want some freaking water,
that's all.
>> I'd say Erica panicked today.
You know, she was kind of grumpy
and screaming, which is all
right, because we always... you
know, lot of us are.
But not at the challenges, you
know?
She's screaming, she's yelling
at people about pieces, this and
that, when it wasn't even her
place to be there.
>> Mookie's probably going to be
my partner in crime, you know.
We pretty much made an alliance,
and that way we can manipulate
everybody and just get it done.
I know it sounds bad, bro, but
what am I going to do?
What am I going to do?
All right, come up here so I can
talk to you.
Come on.
So we're switching it out, bro.
>> Oh, we're switching it out?
>> Yeah.
So Erica is going to go now, and
if and when the next time we
lose, Sylvia goes next.
>> Wouldn't you rather get rid
of Sylvia now?
>> No, no, because Erica is the
threat.
Sylvia is not.
>> Yeah, but we've got to get...
we need the strength is the
thing.
>> To be honest with you, I love
her to death, but I can't always
read her.
I don't always know where she's
coming from.
>> So you'd rather have Sylvia
here?
>> No, Sylvia is next.
>> But we need to take out
Erica.
>> Oh, no.
>> She broke down today.
She... when we had those poles
in, when it didn't work, we
should have taken it out, she's
like, "No, do it again."
>> Mookie said "We're going to
vote Erica off."
I said, "Whoa!"
>> Things change real quick.
>> Yeah, they do.
>> Gee, I thought my days were
numbered here.
Bye.
If you have laundry, just bring
it to us.
And the one thing I learned, if
nothing else, is when you're in
a situation like this, a
survival situation, rule number
one-- you keep your head.
She was panicking and screaming
in my ear.
>> Explain to him, because he's
upset about it, and I don't
blame him.
>> She was completely in a
panic.
You have to stay calm as a team.
When one person's yelling and
screaming, we're all distracted.
>> It's nothing personal, bro.
>> It's just performance.
>> I know it's not personal.
I know it's not personal.
>> I'm telling you.
>> Do you want to keep losing or
no?
It's up to you.
>> Dude, do I look like I want
to keep losing?
>> I'm just asking you, bro.
>> Do you want to ask me that
question again?
>> Do you want to keep losing?
Don't get all mad at me,
brother.
>> I'm not getting mad at you.
>> You're bickering with me for
no reason.
>> I'm not bickering with you.
Dude, I'm not bickering.
>> Okay.
>> You're upset, guy.
>> I'm upset at the whole
situation.
>> Who would you rather it be?
>> I'm upset about the whole
situation, man.
This sucks.
>> You know, Erica lost her top.
She completely blew her stack at
the challenge today.
And because she panicked,
everybody saw it.
And those who didn't trust her a
lot now just want her gone,
which in many ways I think is a
mistake for the tribe.
I don't think it's smart.
>> No, I don't think so, either,
but then....
>> Right, it's the majority.
>> It's the majority.
>> Okay, well...
>> They've got the votes.
They've got the votes.
>> They have enough already?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, if they have enough
already, let me put Sylvia, so I
can be like, "I'm voting you
because I don't like you."
>> Okay, then that's cool.
Then I'll vote for Sylvia, too.
I'm playing the game.
So is everybody else.
You just have to play with what
cards you're dealt.
And right now I've got a really
funky hand.
Getting rid of Sylvia in a lot
of ways would probably be good,
you know, mental health for all
of us.
We were all fine before she
showed up.
We were actually all pretty
tight before she showed up.
>> Here's my question.
How did you feel before she got
here and after she got here?
>> It was just kind of weird
when she got here.
>> That's what I mean.
How did you feel before?
>> I was cool.
>> I thought before we were...
>> We were all good with who we
had, you know?
>> I mean, I feel like we have
the right combination between
the girls and the guys that we
have to make it through.
>> Well, if we keep it together
and if you and I keep together,
then we'll be good.
So we'll do it, and we'll...
>> Okay.
>> We get all the bad luck for
losing, huh?
>> Any more?
>> If we landed in Bizarro World
and we end up with a split vote
of four for Erica and four for
Sylvia, I think a couple of
people's heads would explode.
That would be a whole lot of
people who have been lying to a
whole lot of other people who
are already lying to a whole lot
of other people.
Gives me cramps in my brain to
think about.
I'm just hoping that we're not
in Bizarro World, and everybody
keeps up with what they're
planning to do, because, you
know, in this game, you can't
take anything at face value.
>> PROBST: Mookie, back-to-back
losses in winner-take-all
challenges.
How big of a hole is this tribe
in right now?
>> We're in a deep hole.
We still have no fire, which
means no water.
We're running out of coconuts.
We're tired.
We're in a hole.
We need to win.
>> PROBST: Anthony, what do you
think went wrong in today's
challenge?
>> I think there was too many
people trying to help out in
things where they should have
backed off and let the original
people who we thought were going
to take care of it take care of
it.
>> PROBST: What I saw today,
Erica, was you at one point
screaming, "It goes like this!
It goes like this!"
Can that be an interference?
>> A lot of people tried a lot
of different pieces, and I was
really trying to help out, give
some input.
I'm passionate about my team.
I'm passionate about winning.
And I feel like putting my input
in wasn't such a bad thing, and
all I asked them to do was to go
back and try it again.
>> PROBST: Sylvia, you divide
these tribes, then you leave.
You come back.
Did you feel welcomed?
>> Actually, I felt kind of like
an outsider.
They had the challenge itself,
and then going back to camp,
putting it together, and then
having to come here, and that's
a lot of bonding.
So by the time I showed up, I
felt I was on the outside.
>> PROBST: Rocky, what was your
reaction to Sylvia coming back
and joining the tribe?
>> Sylvia is used to leading.
She's used to, you know,
dictating and telling people
what to do.
But whatever she tries to put
across, she's doing it in a
positive way.
>> PROBST: Anthony, is what
Rocky said true?
Is Sylvia more of a leader?
>> Bless you, Sylvia.
You have a wonderful habit of
kind of throwing out an idea and
saying, "Let's do it," and not
actually talking with anybody
about doing it.
>> PROBST: So, again, Sylvia,
people are saying you're
somewhat of a leader.
Is this surprising to you?
>> A little, because I came in
late.
So I could not be the leader
just walking in off Exile Island
and say, "Okay, everybody, clear
the way.
I'm leader."
But I can offer ideas.
An idea that's been gurgling in
my head, which I haven't brought
up to everybody, but tomorrow
when we're fresh, when we wake
up, is to assign a leader.
>> PROBST: So Yau-Man, last
tribal council it was "Let's get
rid of the weakest member, make
our tribe stronger."
What's the criteria this time
for voting somebody out?
>> The criteria this time I
think is to have a more cohesive
tribe, to form a tribe where we
get along better and be open to
discussion and get rid of
someone who is too vocal or too
stubborn, who is too arrogant
about things.
>> PROBST: Okay, before we get
to the vote, here are the rules
about the hidden immunity idol.
It is good through the final
five.
If you decide to play it, you
will do so after the votes have
been cast, but before I read
them.
You can also give it to someone
else at that point.
If the person who uses the idol
does in fact have the highest
number of votes, then the person
with the next highest number of
votes would be sent home.
Okay, it is time to vote.
Erica, you're up.
>> I just can't read you
anymore.
And quite frankly you're the
biggest threat right now.
Sorry, baby.
>> I'm voting for you because
you've been a little bit pushy
for me.
I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: If anyone has the
idol and wants to play it, now
is the time to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Erica.
Sylvia.
Erica.
Two vote Erica, one vote Sylvia.
Sylvia.
Two votes Sylvia, two votes
Erica.
That's three votes Erica.
Four votes Erica, two votes
Sylvia.
Second person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji.
Erica, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Not much to say.
This tribe has to find a way to
win.
Once again, you will be going
back to camp without fire.
Grab your stuff.
Head on out.
Good night.
>> PROBST: stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time
on Survivor:
Sylvia digs for immunity.
>> I'm pretty sure I know where
the idol is.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: Ravu sparks a flame.
>> We're not going to die!
>> We finally got the shot in
the ass we needed.
>> PROBST: And a Moto member is
in trouble.
>> He can't breathe.
He was afraid.
He said he didn't want to die in
Fiji.
>> I was very, very shocked by
the vote tonight.
It kind of hurts to get
blindsided like that.
I don't think it was a smart
move to vote off somebody who
was strong.
When the next challenge comes
around, I hope you guys win, but
if you don't, I want you to
think about voting me off and
think about who you kept.
And if you go home empty-handed
maybe you should think about the
decision that you made.