>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> Come here.
Hurry, hurry.
>> This is going too great.
>> Yeah, it's, like, too good to
be true, man.
>> PROBST: Moto continued to
grow stronger.
>> It's not even survival, it's
thrival.
>> PROBST: While Ravu became
weaker and weaker.
Until the sun came out-- then
Ravu transformed its rays into
fire.
>> Awesome!
>> We're not going to die!
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, Gary took a hard
fall, but Moto still came out
ahead.
>> Dre scores for Moto!
>> PROBST: Giving Moto more
fishing gear and widening the
gap between the two tribes.
>> Sylvia.
>> PROBST: Sylvia was sent to
Exile Island where she received
a pivotal clue to the
whereabouts of the idol hidden
back at camp.
>> "You'll find it under the
cave's threshold if you dig
deep."
I need to figure out a time and
a place to look for the idol as
quickly as possible.
>> PROBST: At Moto...
>> He can't breathe.
>> PROBST: ...Gary was beginning
to feel ill.
>> We're going to keep a close
eye on him.
His health is more important
than the game to us.
>> PROBST: But at the immunity
challenge...
Papa Smurf starting on his
second snout.
Gary pulled through when Anthony
was unable to chew a pig snout.
Moto wins immunity again!
Before tribal council...
>> Does he irk you at all, or
no?
He seems a little on the whiny
side.
>> PROBST: ...Anthony and Sylvia
were both on the hot seat, and
Sylvia's only hope was finding
the hidden immunity idol.
>> If I get the idol and if the
vote does go my way, I will be
able to surprise everybody.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Anthony questioned his position
in the tribe.
>> I often wonder if these folks
even like me.
I like to think they like me,
but, you know, sometimes you
can't tell.
>> PROBST: Mookie, what's your
thought on what Anthony said?
>> After the challenge, I was
really pissed off.
When you take a little piece of
snout this small, you can will
yourself to throw it down.
>> PROBST: But when Sylvia
failed to produce the idol, she
was voted out of the game.
Sylvia, the tribe has spoken.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> We going to start a fire or
what?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's just get the fire
going.
We will talk about whatever
needs to be talked about, get it
all out.
Just all this silly stuff just
has to go.
When we came back to camp, I
wanted us all to have a powwow.
I mean, people have problems
with certain people, personality
problems, and they don't say
anything.
So that other person doesn't
know.
So this just keeps on going and
pressure builds up and then
people explode.
We'll start talking.
>> All of us start talking?
>> Start talking, man.
>> Start talking.
What would you like to talk
about?
>> Start talking.
>> I don't want to be involved
in bitching and moaning and
screaming.
>> Certain people want to bitch
and moan, though.
>> But guy, that's all he ( no
audio ) does.
>> Reacting like that, that's
just...
>> Reacting like what?
>> Just chill, for real.
>> You have no idea how much I'm
holding back, especially with
Anthony, you know what I mean?
Sitting around dealing with
somebody you really can't tell
him how you feel because you're
worried about his vote.
Right now I could care less
about his vote.
For some reason, Anthony, you
consistently irritate the ( no
audio ) out of me all the ( no
audio ) time.
And I think you go out of your
way to do it.
I think you go out of your way
to do it.
I think, for some reason, for
some strange reason, you play
the sympathy case once in a
while that drives me nuts.
I don't usually deal with people
like that unless it's a broad--
no offense to ladies, that's how
I talk to girls-- unless it's a
girl or it's my mother or it's
my crazy aunt.
Everybody messes up, but when
you whine about something or you
get all, like... you get all,
like, sentimental and
sensitive... you're a man.
At least, the way I was raised,
I'm a man, I've got to act like
one.
>> I'm sorry I irk you, and I'm
sorry I irritate you.
I have no idea what I'm doing to
you that's irritating you.
I've spent a lot of my life with
very little self-esteem.
You know, I got picked on as a
kid, and I guess I developed a
whole lot of self-loathing.
>> I got along with Jessica.
I got along with Erica.
Those two people are gone, and
you're still here driving me
absolutely insane.
Both of those girls, better
players than you.
No offense.
Some people have it, some people
don't.
>> I may not be doing the best
in the challenges, but if they
want me off this island, they
want me out of this game,
they're going to have to push me
off.
Because there's no way in hell
I'm giving up.
>> Wow, I'm in Fiji.
This is gorgeous.
It's absolutely breathtaking.
And at night with the moon is
out...
>> Which makes our thing so
perfect, you know?
>> Right.
Yeah.
The five musketeers.
>> From the beginning there has
been a bond between Boo, Alex,
Edgar, myself, and Stacy.
It's almost been unspoken.
All we know is that the five of
us get along and we're not
stepping on each other's toes.
We all kind of come together.
It's just amazing how things
have just, like, fallen into
place.
>> The other team must be
kicking their asses right now.
>> That's the way the cookie
crumbles.
>> This water is awesome!
I just want that cloud to go
away.
>> So Gary...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I've done a lot of miserable
things in my life.
I mean, I did a tour of Vietnam
and we had some crap that wasn't
no fun either.
But gee whiz, this is just...
the head spinning is just... I
can't... you can't function.
>> Everybody loves Gary in the
tribe, and definitely want him
to keep competing if he feels
good enough, but I think he
should take his health first.
At his age, the amount of stress
and possibly high blood
pressure... I want him to feel
better, first of all.
>> You have so many bites, Gary.
>> Mm-hmm.
You've got thousands of them.
Gary does not look good at all,
and eventually it's going to
turn into, like, a babysitting
situation.
It's like, "Okay, you know, did
I just have a baby and didn't
realize it?"
Did you have some of that
coconut meat?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> You should have some, have
plenty.
I really don't want to take care
of him.
I don't want to babysit.
So let's hope he gets better.
That's the only thing I can say.
If he doesn't get better he's
going have to go.
>> PROBST: Moto, come on in!
Ravu, come on in!
Moto getting your first look at
the new Ravu tribe.
Sylvia voted out at the last
tribal council.
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yep.
>> Yeah, we are.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, both tribes will line
up side by side on a very narrow
balance beam over water.
Moving one tribe member at a
time, you must make your way
across the beam, stepping around
your tribemates as you go.
If you fall off, or if you are
knocked off, you go back to the
start.
Once you get off the beam, onto
the finish platform, then the
next tribe member goes.
You can change your crossing
order mid challenge, but you
have to jump in the water to
do so.
First tribe to get all their
tribemates offof the beam,
on to the finish platform, win
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: It's another big one.
>> Oh, man!
>> PROBST: Whole lot of fish.
>> Fish, yeah.
>> PROBST: Plenty of rice.
Spices to liven up everything
you eat.
Plus some comfort-- pillows,
blankets.
That's not all.
Waiting back at camp for the
winning tribe, a king-sized bed
with sheets and pillows.
In addition, the winning tribe
will send one member from the
losing tribe to Exile Island.
Moto, you have two extra
members.
Who are you going to sit out?
>> Cassandra and Papa Smurf.
>> PROBST: Gary and Cassandra,
sitting this one out.
Swim out.
We'll get started.
Once you guys are set, you
cannot be holding onto each
other.
The only person you can touch is
the person that's crossing you.
The wind is starting to pick up.
Perfect time to begin this
challenge.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Michelle for Ravu makes her way
around Yau-Man.
Stacy working around Lisi.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Both going in.
Michelle working Rita now.
Stacy and Lisi are trying to get
back up.
Big reward on the line.
Stacy tries a new approach.
And that knocks Lisi off.
There's a learning curve to this
challenge.
You will figure it out as you go
along.
Michelle making good progress.
She's halfway through.
Dreamz has a new idea.
Your hands cannot touch the
beam.
Lisi steps over Stacy.
Michelle hugging her way past
Rocky.
Lisi stepping over Alex.
Both going in.
Michelle easily sidesteps around
Earl, the first tribe member
across for Ravu.
>> Lisi, let's go, baby, both of
your hands on Alex.
>> PROBST: Moto going to stick
with their strategy.
Yau-Man now working around Rita.
Gingerly, but it's effective.
Lisi now going to have to
sidestep a much taller guy, and
she can't do it.
Lisi back to the start.
Yau-Man crosses for Ravu.
Ravu leads 2-0.
Moto has a very precise strategy
they're trying to work out.
No, Lisi, you can't touch two
people.
One at a time, one at a time.
Rita now working for Ravu.
>> You can do it!
You can do it!
>> PROBST: Lisi still trying to
be the first member across for
Moto.
Rita and Anthony still working
it.
>> Use your hands and put your
weight on him but make sure it's
balanced.
>> PROBST: Lisi, one member left
to get over.
Lisi across for Moto.
It's two-one.
Anthony and Rita have been
locked in an embrace for a long
time.
Anthony falls off, a lot of
progress lost for Ravu.
Moto's strategy is starting to
work.
Alex over Boo.
Moto has tied at two-two.
>> Come on, come on!
>> PROBST: Mookie and Anthony,
going to have to work together.
Mookie and Anthony both fall in.
Stacy trying to figure out how
she's going to get over Edgardo.
Edgardo jumps in.
All kinds of strategy coming
into play.
>> Everyone fall in.
Everyone fall in!
Earl, stay.
Come on, come on!
>> PROBST: Ravu changing their
entire lineup.
Half the tribe jumps in to give
the stronger people a better
shot.
But Anthony can't even stay up
on the beam.
>> ( groaning )
>> ( cheers )
>> PROBST: Edgardo scores for
Moto.
We are three-two, Moto now in
the lead.
Ravu now using Moto's strategy.
Mookie, you can only touch one
at a time.
Think.
Get in the water.
Liliana making it look easy.
Moto leads four-two.
Ravu still working.
Dreamz is across.
It is five-two.
Stacy across for Moto.
Boo gives a wave to the crowd.
Moto wins reward!
Ravu, once again, early lead,
lost it in the end.
Moto, still undefeated in
challenges, and a big decision
to make.
Sending one person to Exile
Island.
They will return in time for the
next immunity challenge.
Who's it going to be?
>> Yau-Man.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man going to
Exile Island, where you will
find another clue to the
whereabouts of the hidden
immunity idol.
Moto-- fish, rice, spices, and
waiting back at camp, a king-
sized bed.
Congratulations.
Ravu, once again, got nothing
for you.
Head back to camp.
>> Yeah!
>> This is great!
>> Look at the size of this
fish!
>> Today we once again kicked
the crap out of Ravu, and in the
process, won ourselves a bed,
which I am so excited about.
>> Oh, my god.
>> We can fit five people in
here, man.
>> Not only to we have comfort
with the cushions and the
blankets, but the fish that we
got, and the seasoning, I was
like, "Oh, my gosh, I'm in
heaven."
>> Here, pull these spices off.
>> Man, soy sauce!
>> Paprika.
>> I know.
>> Okay, what you all got?
>> Oregano.
>> We're just living lovely
right now.
Our morale is up now more than
ever.
>> Geez, man, we're going to eat
like kings today.
>> Oh, man!
>> Motolicious.
>> I feel sorry for the
individual members of the other
tribe, but I want us to continue
winning.
I... I don't want to let up for
a second.
>> Absolutely ridiculous!
Five in a row?
Five in a row we lose?
>> What do you want to do?
Do you want to get together and
talk about it, or...
>> Thank you!
Why don't we just go to tribal
council right now?
You want to go to tribal council
right now, we'll vote somebody
off?
Because that's all we do every
week.
Every other day we vote somebody
off.
So why don't we call Jeff up
right now on the Jeff phone and
go, "Hey, Jeff, we're ready to
vote somebody off today."
I'm skinnier than homeless
people right now.
I know 15 homeless people that
are 40 pounds heavier than me.
Are you serious?
They're getting more nutrition
in their diet.
That's it right there.
That was it.
Food, pillows, a bed.
Everything we complain about
every day and we couldn't muster
it up.
Tell me why.
>> We just lost.
>> So what's the sense?
What's the sense of going, "Oh,
we'll get them next time, oh,
we'll do this next time"?
No.
I'm not sugarcoating nothing.
>> We lost, it sucks, let's move
on.
I mean, if you go in somewhere
thinking you're going to lose,
your chances are...
>> I'm not being negative.
I'm stating the obvious.
There's a difference.
>> Who's going to get more wood?
>> I like Rocky's spirit but
it's not all about just talk.
It's about motivating.
Like, do something-- not just at
challenges but here on this
island.
>> Argh!
>> I'm starving!
>> We have an interesting tribe.
>> I'm hungry, I'm tired, I'm
thirsty, but do I still get my
ass up and go do something?
Yeah.
But I'm telling you now, I can
already feel this one.
>> I already know how it's going
to go.
If we lose tomorrow, you know
whose name's going down?
It's going to be me.
I know I have a big target on
me, and I know that I have to be
careful and patient.
But now that I've gotten a
better grasp on who James is,
I'll let him keep talking,
because really in the end it
makes him look like an ass.
If you don't like your bed, fix
it.
Chop down some palm fronds.
I trust Anthony.
I think he's a good guy, he's a
genuine guy.
But it's getting harder to look
out for him.
But I haven't made my exact move
yet of what I'm going to do.
I'm still devising the plan.
>> "Here you won't find the idol
you crave.
It's buried under the highest
point of the big cave."
I'm not resentful at all of Moto
for sending me here.
In a way, I'm glad I get a
chance to find the immunity
idol.
Highest point through which you
enter.
So it must be at the entrance.
We may be sleeping on it.
I'm quite sure I know where the
idol is.
The problem, of course, is when
do I get the chance to dig
alone?
I need the immunity idol very
badly, so I'll see how fast I
can dig.
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa!
( laughter )
>> Liliana knows what she's
doing, and sometimes guys aren't
hip to the way chicks maneuver.
It's funny, because Liliana
tries to be so sneaky, but I'm
Latin, and knowing my people the
way that I do, I see what she's
doing.
I know in her little diabolical
Mexican mind she's trying to
come up with something, you
know?
>> Oh, my god!
( laughter )
>> Wow!
What in the world?
>> It just seems like the whole
world is caving in here.
I don't got the energy to do
nothing.
I just can't... I can't
function.
>> How you doing, big guy?
Feeling nauseated?
>> I ain't never had nothing
like this before.
I've had malaria ages ago, and
that's nothing compared to
what's going on.
It just kind of scares you a
little bit, you know?
I just don't have...
>> Hi, Gary.
>> I'm very worried for Papa
Smurf, because I can see Papa
Smurf was real hurt.
Papa Smurf is one of the only
people I talk to, so that's kind
of worrying me.
>> All right.
>> I'm not so concerned about
whether Gary stays in the game
or not.
Quite frankly, one less person,
you know, means greater odds for
all of us.
>> Good-bye, Papa Smurf.
>> Bye, Gary!
>> Today was very frustrating,
to be honest with you.
We lost Gary, and... I don't
know.
I feel... I don't feel good
about it.
I don't feel good about today at
all.
>> Bye, Papa Smurf!
>> Love you!
>> I hope to god we don't lose
the next immunity challenge
tomorrow.
But if we lose that immunity
challenge, we're 7-7.
In the eyes of the game, we're
tied, and then we're screwed.
>> I'm going crazy, bro.
I'm going crazy, bro.
I just want to start winning.
But all I can do is the best I
can and try to get people fired
up.
I can lead by example.
>> We've got tree mail!
>> Are you guys ready?
>> "Some of you are feeling
trapped while others just hang
around.
The key to winning today's event
on your teammates will be found.
Whether you're on the bottom or
if you're on the top, or if
you're..." don't, I don't want
to look at you.
>> Oh, dude.
>> "...the pressure today will
be intense.
Tonight for one this game will
stop."
>> I wasn't even watching.
>> Well, thankfully, I only got
like a half a second peek of
James naked.
Not a pretty sight.
>> Wear one of the girls'
shirts.
>> Do you want my bikini top?
>> I'm trying to make everybody
laugh.
I'm wearing a pink halter top
with some coconuts in it.
Feeling pretty good right now.
>> That's hilarious, man.
>> Anything to get the focus off
losing five in a row, and
hopefully just go out there and
let it loose and win a game.
>> PROBST: Ravu, come on in!
Rocky, Pink is a good color for
you.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
I was hoping you'd enjoy it.
>> PROBST: Ravu has a great
attitude for having not won
anything.
No, that was a complement.
>> Cool.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
Yau-Man returning from Exile
Island.
>> Whoo!
>> I survived!
Thank you.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
Moto.
>> PROBST: Gary, Papa Smurf, was
evacuated yesterday for medical
reasons from Moto's beach.
>> Oh, wow!
>> PROBST: The update is Gary is
officially out of the game, so
Moto has lost their first
member.
>> Oh, no!
>> PROBST: They are now down to
eight.
Despite losing Gary, the game
continues.
I will take back immunity, Alex.
Immunity is back up for grabs.
Ready to get to today's immunity
challenge?
>> Do it.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Four tribe members
will begin locked in floating
cages.
On my "go," another tribe member
will head out with the key to
unlock the first tribe member
from a cage.
Once that person is free, they
must then race across a series
of lily pads to free the second
member from a locked cage.
Once the fourth tribe member is
free from their cage, that tribe
member and the rescuer get onto
a boat where another tribe
member is waiting with a ring of
keys.
Together, you will paddle to
shore, picking up your stranded
tribemates as you go.
Once you're back to shore, you
must then form a human pyramid.
The person on top will use the
ring of keys to unlock that last
cage and free your final tribe
member.
First tribe to get on their
finish mat wins immunity.
Make sense?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: There is one twist to
today's challenge.
Sealed inside this bottle is a
note.
The winning tribe will read this
note after the challenge.
Moto, you're going to have to
sit one person out.
Cannot sit out the same people
in back-to-back challenges.
Cassandra sat out last time.
Who's it going to be this time?
>> We're going to sit out Lisi.
>> PROBST: Lisi, have a spot on
the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize and we'll
get started.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Edgardo with the early lead for
Moto.
>> Come on, Edgardo!
>> Come on, Rocky.
Go, Rocky.
>> Edgardo to the cage first.
>> There you go, there you go.
Rocky loses his keys, falling
behind.
Dreamz is out.
He's on the lily pads.
Dreamz crawling across the lily
pads.
Rocky has Yau-Man out.
>> Come on, Yau.
Come on.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man takes on the
lily pads.
Dreamz working on the lock
trying to get Alex free.
Alex moving on for Moto.
>> Come on, Yau.
Come on, take your time.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man falling
behind for Ravu.
Yau-Man to the platform.
He's got to get up.
>> Good boy, Yau!
Push!
>> PROBST: Moto now one full
platform ahead.
>> You got it, baby.
You got it.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man losing his
had glasses trying to work on
the lot for Rita.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Alex has Boo free!
>> Rita now free.
She's working on the lily pads.
Barely hanging on.
Moto with a big lead now.
>> All right, all right, all
right.
>> Rita, push it, push it!
>> PROBST: Boo has Liliana free.
They're getting on the boat.
>> Go forward, forward, forward.
forward.
>> All right, guys paddle it!
Paddle it!
>> Dig, dig, dig.
There you go.
>> PROBST: Rita losing a lot of
time for Ravu.
>> Get in!
>> Oh, my god!
>> Alex on the boat for Moto.
>> Rita just now at the
platform.
Ravu has a lot of time to make
up.
>> Row, row, row, row!
Ravu not quitting.
>> Dig, dig, dig!
>> PROBST: Mookie making up a
lot of time.
>> Jump in, jump in, jump in!
Dreamz now getting on the boat.
>> All right, here.
Come on.
>> Earl now free.
Ravu now in their boat.
>> Get on!
Get in the middle!
Get in the boat.
>> ( laughing )
>> Come on, Rita!
>> Dig!
Left side, dig.
>> Dig, dig, dig, dig!
>> PROBST: Ravu, keep moving.
Let's go!
Moto heading into shore.
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
>> Come on, Rocky!
>> PROBST: You're still in it,
Ravu.
Let's go!
>> PROBST: Moto starts to work
on their human pyramid.
That top person has got to
stand.
Ravu now back.
Stacy working on the last lock.
There are five keys.
Stacy having trouble with the
lock, trying key after key,
hoping one will fit.
Ravu working on their pyramid.
Ravu back in it, if Michelle
picks the right key.
Immunity plus a twist to be
revealed on the line.
Stacy has to get down and open
the cage.
Moto wins immunity!
Still undefeated!
Moto, congratulations once
again.
>> Good job, guys!
>> PROBST: Now there's one more
element to this challenge-- the
bottle.
As I said, the winning tribe
would open the bottle and read
the note.
Who wants it?
>> "You have just won immunity.
You must now decide which is
more important to you, immunity
or comfort.
To keep your immunity, you must
live at the Ravu tribe camp.
>> Of course.
>> To enjoy the food and comfort
of the Moto camp, you must give
up immunity and vote someone out
tonight."
>> PROBST: So, interesting
dilemma-- which is more
important?
You can keep your tribe strong
at eight, switch camps, go live
on Ravu's beach.
If comfort is more important,
you can stay living where you
are.
You give immunity to Ravu, you
go to tribal council and vote
somebody out, and suddenly we
are even, 7-7.
So all of a sudden, Gary's
departure looming very large for
this tribe.
I'll give you a minute to talk
it over.
>> Who wants to keep the camp?
Raise your hand.
We're going to tribal council
tonight.
>> Jeff, we're keeping our
comfort and going to tribal
council.
>> PROBST: All right, Boo, go
ahead and give immunity to Ravu.
Ravu, for once, you won't be
going to tribal council.
Moto, you'll be going back to
your camp with all the comforts.
I'll see you at tribal.
Grab your stuff, head on back to
camp.
>> We won the challenge, and we
had the option of giving up our
home or vote somebody off.
So unfortunately, we're going to
vote somebody off.
And it's even uglier being that
Gary left yesterday, so it's
kind of like we're losing two
people.
>> All right, let's sit down and
talk for a second.
This is what I feel is very
important to me.
I'm going... I'm not going to
sugarcoat nothing.
I think we are a tribe, right?
We're honest, right?
Are we snakes?
Anybody here a snake?
Not yet.
We ain't snakes yet.
And let's not turn into snakes
yet.
So with that being said and out
of the way, there's two people
we can afford to lose now.
I ain't pointing no fingers.
It's Cassandra and Lisi.
We can only afford to lose them,
right?
Am I right?
If I'm not right, if anybody
objects...
>> It depends on how you look
it.
>> I think that's are the only
two people you can afford to
lose.
>> I'll be sincere.
I'm not going to vote for Lisi.
I like Lisi.
Cassandra, I'm going to be
straight with you.
Probably my vote tonight will be
against you.
>> Here's the thing, Dreamz.
I don't think you can ignore the
interpersonal relationships that
have been built, not because
it's a friendship, but it's also
in thinking long-term, that bond
may help you in the future.
>> We're not individuals yet.
We're still a group.
>> Dreamz started freaking out.
I think he shoots from the hip a
lot, and he's a bit naive.
Because he has no clue what's
going on.
He thinks we're all part of this
solid team, that we do things
together in stride.
And it's not entirely untrue,
it's just that the team consists
of five people-- myself, Alex,
Ed, Lisi, and Boo.
>> If anybody else got something
to say, please.
So is that what we're going to
do?
>> Well we've got to decide
something now before we start,
"Come with me to the water
fountain real quick.
Come with me to..." you know
what I'm saying?
That's when we turn to snakes
and start biting each other.
We don't have to eat each other
yet.
We don't have to do that yet.
Let's not do it yet.
>> I don't know, I don't know.
>> I just want things to go down
fair so we don't have to see the
snake so early.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Like, it's not that we don't
like you and we don't think
you're a good person, because I
think you rock.
>> No, I understand.
>> The thing is, it would be a
backward step for me to go
against what they're doing.
I'm going to try to stay in this
game longer.
>> Yeah.
All I'll say is just, you know,
hang in there.
It could be me going home this
evening after tribal council.
But I don't want to be the first
voted out of my tribe.
I didn't want to be the first
voted out of the game.
So I'm holding on.
>> I think Dreamz is better for
us, so we need to keep Dreamz.
>> We need to keep Dreamz, okay?
>> I vote Liliana, too.
>> Let's do it.
She's going to be like...
As far as I'm concerned, Liliana
is the weakest link.
Because our biggest concern is
to get to the top five, and
she's the one person that could
threaten it.
She could try to manipulate
things.
She could say all sorts of
things that could start tearing
us apart.
>> If we take out Liliana...
Cassandra is bad at everything.
She sucks at everything.
>> It's not... we're not going
to be hurting.
I swear to you.
>> The most logical thing is to
keep Liliana, vote out Cassandra
until we have a numbers
advantage again.
Right now we're 7-7.
Why on god's green earth would
you vote out a woman who is as
strong, almost as any of the
men?
That to me seems absurd.
>> One of them has got to go.
>> I'm voting Liliana.
>> Me, too.
>> I'm very frustrated.
I feel like this is illogical.
I want to do what's best for our
five-person alliance and for the
team in general.
Liliana is a good person.
She's worked hard at these
challenges.
She deserves to stay.
Cassandra should go.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch and
approach the flame.
Dip it in, get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
tribal council, because in this
game, fire represents life.
As long as you have fire, you're
still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
Boo, tell me about the loss of
Gary.
What was the reaction when he
had to leave?
>> Everyone, even the other
tribe, loved Gary.
He was sick for three days, and
he stayed tough for our tribe.
We miss him, and we can't wait
to see him again.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, let's talk
about friendship.
Are you starting to bond with
certain people maybe more than
others?
>> Pretty much Papa Smurf and
Cassandra.
But I'm not going to lie to you.
The rest of them, if I talk they
just get silent or they don't
talk back.
>> PROBST: Edgardo, can you
understand what Dreamz is
saying?
>> I really don't know where
he's coming from.
I think we all, you know, treat
each other the same way.
You know, I treat Liliana the
same way I treat Dreamz or Boo.
But if he feels that way, I'm
going to make sure he doesn't
feel that way anymore.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's challenge.
Lisi, in spite of the fact that
you won, you have to come to
tribal council.
So what happens at camp?
>> As a matter of fact, Dreamz
goes on a soliloquy about how,
you know, some people should be
voted off, the weakest ones...
>> Jeff...
>> Cassandra and Lisi.
So he's talking about being
indivisible, but he's pointing
fingers.
Hello!
>> PROBST: So, Dreamz, you come
back to camp and you decide,
"Let's just have a powwow and
I'm going tell you how it is."
>> Well, not like that, Jeff.
Don't make me sound like a
monster.
>> PROBST: I'm asking!
>> All right.
I was just saying, "Stop me if
I'm wrong, if y'all think I'm
wrong at any point in time."
Nobody stopped me, Jeff.
They let me go on a shaquila, or
whatever she called it.
>> PROBST: Soliloquy.
>> She let me go on a soliloquy,
or whatever they call it.
I didn't want to eat each other
yet, you know what I'm saying?
I didn't want people to go off
into little groups and start
talking about people.
>> PROBST: So Alex, you didn't
lose, but you're here.
You don't want to vote somebody
out, but you have to.
What do you base it on?
>> I think you base it on what's
going to be best for the tribe
moving forward, and we're going
to just move on and do whatever
it takes to make sure that Ravu
doesn't have another opportunity
to have one of our members voted
out.
>> PROBST: Liliana, what do you
bring to this tribe?
>> I feel that I bring strength,
and I try to get with the guys
and say, "Let's go fishing or
hunting or climbing."
So helping the guys out is not a
problem for me.
That's just the way I am at
home, and I'm here being the
same person.
>> PROBST: Cassandra.
>> I definitely want to
compliment Liliana.
She's exemplary for the female
strength.
She's just amazing.
I just look for her to go very
far in the game.
Love you.
>> Love you, too.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Alex, you're up.
>> I'm going to really miss you.
You're such a great person.
I really did see the strength in
you.
>> The alliance is five, not
six.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Liliana.
Lisi.
One vote Liliana, one vote Lisi.
Cassandra.
That's one vote each for
Liliana, Lisi, and Cassandra.
Liliana.
Two votes Liliana.
That's three votes Liliana, one
vote Lisi, one vote Cassandra.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji, Liliana.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> I'm so shocked.
So shocked.
If they didn't get me out now, I
was going to beat them.
>> PROBST: Liliana, the tribe
has spoken.
>> PROBST: Well, I think
Liliana's expression said it
all.
This game definitely being
played within the Moto tribe.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Those two are two sour
apples.
>> PROBST: Moto begins to
fracture.
>> PROBST: The hunt for the idol
is on.
>> I got a chance to dig.
I don't know for how long.
>> Laugh it up.
>> Why don't me and you go up
there right now?
>> We could.
>> Let's do that then.
Keep running your mouth.
Bring it.
>> PROBST: And the gloves come
off.
>> Well, I'm definitely 100%
shocked.
To me, it's ridiculous to get
rid of one of your stronger
people in the beginning.
I just wish I could have stayed
in longer, because I definitely
would have kicked some butt.
Wow, there are some good liars,
great liars.
I think the weak link stayed
behind and not... the strong
one's leaving today.