>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> Water!
>> Just lick some leaves, man.
>>PROBST: Life at Ravu was
bleak.
>> I never experienced
dehydration like this.
Half of us can't even stand up.
It's crazy!
We're starving here, bro.
>> Life at Moto was carefree.
>> We have a really plush couch.
We are very fortunate to be
living the way that we're
living.
>> Boo, be careful!
>> PROBST: And Boo got careless.
>> Boo is a real hazard to
hisself, and he will hurt
hisself out of the game.
>> Sylvia.
>> Is she here?
>> PROBST: Sylvia joined Ravu
after a night on Exile Island.
>> Welcome home!
When I went up to greet her, I
was actually quite nasty.
I look over her shoulder, and
I open up her shoulder bag to
see if she found the immunity
idol.
>> Tonight, we ought to go out
and get some oysters.
>> PROBST: But her presence
brought on new frustrations.
>> I was not really excited for
Sylvia to come back.
I personally think she's a
little bossy.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
>> I'm pulling out the...
>> PROBST: Erica's certain she's
right!
Erica spoke up, while Moto
pulled ahead.
Moto wins the challenge!
Moto.
Moto took home fishing supplies,
and banished Earl, who battled
the serpents on Exile Island.
Facing Tribal Council...
>> PROBST: ...Mooky and Rocky
turned against Erica...
>> Now you want Erica, huh?
She freaked out.
>> PROBST: ...blaming her for
Ravu's loss.
>> She was screaming, she's on
people about peace and this
and that, when it wasn't even
her place to be there.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council...
>> Sylvia is used to dictating
and telling people what to do.
>> PROBST: ...Sylvia's
personality was scrutinized.
>> You have a habit of
kind of throwing out an idea and
saying, "Let's do it," and not
actually talking with anybody.
>> PROBST: But it was Erica
whose torch was snuffed.
Erica, the tribe has spoken.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> The two back-to-back losses
have really affected us, and
this last Tribal Council was
very brutal.
We came to a realization that
we are quite... not quite
connected together yet as a
tribe.
>> First thing in the morning,
let's cut some coconuts, get
some... get hydrated, cut some
pineapples.
>> I would like to, if I see
big sun, if I could try and
start a fire.
>> Yeah, I'll be out there on
the beach with you, too, with
some glasses.
>> Being the biggest group of
losers that Survivor has ever
seen sucks!
It's no fun.
We can't win challenges right
now; I don't know what it is.
I don't know if they put,
like, a jinx on us or a curse,
but we just can't win right now.
Let's say we do have a challenge
tomorrow, okay?
I'm not telling you what to do.
I'm just throwing out a
suggestion.
Maybe... maybe, like, somebody
could just-- not even take
charge-- just one person can
talk at a time.
When everybody talks over each
other, it doesn't work.
>> Right.
>> At this point, we still have
the desire to win, but we
really need to get our act
together and have a good
strategy going in.
>> Let's put egos aside and put
tribe and winning first, and
just, you know, have...
We've got to try.
>> The more we lose, the more
difficult it is to recover.
(theme song playing)
>> This is going to dry real
quick.
>> Looks nice, huh?
>> It's pretty.
>> I like it.
>> Lisi suggested that we paint
the floor to kind of seal up the
wood to prevent the ants from
coming in.
It will look nice, but there's
a function to it.
>> It looks pretty, but it
wasn't done with the intention
for aesthetics.
I'll bet the ant lines are going
to be a lot less tonight.
>> Hurry, hurry, to the pot.
>> Very good.
>> Oh, they're perfect.
>> This is going too great.
>> Yeah. It's, like, too good to
be true, man.
>> We gotta take a poll.
>> Are we really on Survivor,
or are we dreaming?
>> We're just having a party
out here, really.
We're telling jokes, lounging
around on a hammock.
We don't have to win anything
else as far as survival.
It's not even survival.
It's "thrive-al."
>> I really wouldn't be
surprised if the people on the
other side just started dropping
like flies because they
just don't seem to be catching a
break, man.
>> Big Earl!
>> Ravu!
>> Welcome home!
>> You guys got a fire?
>> No.
The sun, we seen it today, man.
>> But you got some water,
sweetie?
>> I'm back from Exile Island.
The first thing they asked me,
"Do you have water?"
It was like walking on the
beach to a bunch of begging
children.
>> Was the clue really obscure?
>> The clue is interesting.
As far as the immunity idol, I
sure have no idea where it is.
I mean, I don't know how it
really works, with the clue
thing, like, I mean, you guys
probably know more than I do.
I mean, I have to give more
thought, and really survey the
land.
It's under something that's
high, and it can be anywhere,
but I'll figure something out.
Losing-- it hurts.
Yeah, I mean, come on.
It's, like, no fire again?
We're trying to take advantage
of any of this sun or are we
just, like, dead?
>> Now we're waiting for the
point where it gets up high
enough.
>> Dear Sun, Michelle would
like you to come out and play
today.
Please participate in my game.
Sincerely, Michelle.
>> It's coming out.
It's going to come out.
>> Yeah.
We haven't had fire, so I
decided to just go out and give
it a go while we have some sun.
The sun's moving fast, oh, geez.
Using glasses to start a fire
is absolutely possible.
I started to pray, because I
know my momma doesn't want me
to die out here.
Come on.
Burn, baby, burn.
Whoo!
I looked down about a minute
and a half later, and I see the
start of a fire, so I go running
back to the beach.
First person I see is Anthony,
and I hand that off to him.
I'm, like, "Start a fire with
this."
>> Fire!
>> Fire?
>> Help.
>> Oh, here, here, here, here.
>> I got to go.
Where am I going?
>> Oh, my God.
>> There you go.
>> Give me some tinders.
>> Somebody blow, somebody blow.
Gentle, gentle.
Anything you got here, get it
going, come on.
(cheering)
>> Awesome.
(cheering, whooping)
>> We're not gonna die.
>> We've been struggling a long
time, and now we finally got a
shot in the ass that we needed,
so I think it's going to be a
good day.
I'd be scared to be the other
team right now because we're,
we're just so fired up, it's
ridiculous.
>> PROBST: Moto, come on in.
Ravu, come on in.
Moto, getting your first look at
the new Ravu tribe.
Erica voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Ravu, last time I talked to you
guys, life was not enjoyable.
Rocky, things still tough over
there?
>> Uh, things are tough, but,
but they're getting better.
My, uh, my girl Michelle over
here started a fire today...
boiled some water; things are
looking up.
>> PROBST: You started fire?
>> Yes.
>> Michelle did, yes, we did.
>> PROBST: Ravu, I got to say
you have done what very few
tribes have ever done in this
game, which is start fire on
your own.
Congratulations.
Because you have fire, you no
longer have to earn it.
Here's your flint.
(cheering)
You now have your flint, same as
Moto.
Hopefully, you'll be able to
keep your fire going.
All right, for today's reward
challenge, you will race head-
to-head as you slide down a
slippery course to retrieve a
numbered ball that I will
randomly assign each round.
First tribe member to toss your
ball into a basket scores a
point for their tribe.
First tribe to six wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> ALL: Yeah!
>> PROBST: You will have a
choice.
First reward you might choose is
a little taste of home in the
form of your luxury items.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: If that's not
whetting your appetite...
(gasping, murmuring)
...an exact duplicate set of the
fishing gear that Moto won.
If you don't like either of
those, third choice: instant
gratification-- fresh fruit.
In addition, the winning tribe
will send one member from the
losing tribe to Exile Island.
This time, however, that person
will not be immune.
They will rejoin their tribe
before the next challenge.
Moto, because you have one extra
member, you're sitting somebody
out.
>> I want to sit out.
>> PROBST: Lisi going to sit
out.
Lisi, you'll take a spot on the
bench; everybody else,
we'll get started.
>> PROBST: For the first round,
it will be Anthony for Ravu;
Gary, Papa Smurf, for Moto.
You are going for number nine.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Gary!
(teams shouting)
>> PROBST: Gary trying to run,
takes a hard fall.
Anthony sliding his way across.
Gary and Anthony both tiptoeing.
Oh! Gary takes another one,
hard.
>> Go, Gary, go!
>> PROBST: Got to get it in the
basket.
>> Come on, Ravu!
>> PROBST: First one to get it
in scores a point for their
tribe.
Gary scores for Moto!
Moto leads, one-zero.
Next round will be two women.
For Ravu, it is Rita taking on
Cassandra.
For Moto, going for number
three.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, go!
>> Go, Rita!
>> PROBST: Rita and Cassandra
heading for number three.
Oh! Cassandra takes a hard fall
and turns it into a great slide!
Cassandra has her ball.
She knocks off Rita's.
Cassandra's trying to stay up.
Rita trying to stay up.
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: Got to get it in the
bucket.
Moto leads, one-zip.
Choice of rewards on the line.
Ravu scores!
Rita scores for Ravu.
We're tied, one-one.
Next round will be Boo for Moto
taking on Rocky for Ravu.
You're going for number seven.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Rocky and Boo.
Boo getting a big sprint.
Paddling right to number seven,
grabs it on his way and heads
to the basket.
Rocky takes a fall right behind.
Boo with one shot, scores for
Moto!
Moto leads, two-one.
That is how you do it.
Next round will be Michelle
taking on Stacy for Moto.
You are going for number six.
Survivors ready?
Go!
(teams shouting)
Stacy really working that slide,
every bit of it.
She's got her ball and drops it
and falls.
Michelle has hers and drops it.
They're both gingerly tiptoeing.
To the shooting line.
Michelle tosses.
She's short.
Stacy just misses for Moto.
Michelle just misses for Ravu.
Stacy bounces it off the net!
Moto leads, three-one.
Next round will be Alex for
Moto taking on Mookie for Ravu.
>> Let's go, Mookie!
>> PROBST: You are going for
number ten.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's a sprint.
Mookie launches himself.
Alex surfing across the course.
Mookie has his ball.
Alex has his and drops it and
falls.
Mookie gets off a shot, but it's
missed.
Mookie scores for Ravu!
Moto leads, three-two.
Next round will be Sylvia for
Ravu taking on Liliana from
Moto.
Going for number two.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Liliana!
>> PROBST: Oh!
Sylvia takes a hard fall.
Liliana right on target.
She's got her ball, and she's
heading to the shooting line.
Sylvia struggling to get to her
ball.
A big lead for Liliana.
Sylvia walking very gingerly,
tiptoeing her way across this
course.
Giving Liliana a lot of free
shots.
Sylvia still not at the
shooting line.
Liliana scores for Moto!
Moto leads, four-two.
Next round will be Earl for
Ravu taking on Edgardo for Moto.
Going for number 11.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Edgardo out of the gate quickly.
Earl catches up quickly.
Both guys now on their feet.
Edgardo's got his ball.
Earl has his.
Edgardo launches his first shot
and misses.
Earl taking his time...
and just misses for Ravu.
Edgardo scores for Moto!
Moto leads, five-two.
Next round, Yau-Man for Ravu
against Dre for Moto.
>> (laughs loudly)
>> PROBST: Moto leads, five-two.
It takes six to win.
Dre could win it right here for
Moto.
Yau-Man trying to keep Ravu in
it.
You are going for number five.
Survivors ready?
Go!
(teams shouting)
Yau-Man right in this with Dre.
Dre has his ball.
Yau-Man has his.
Yau-Man looking very light on
his feet.
Dre misses short.
Yau-Man with a nice toss, just
misses.
>> Come on, Dre!
>> PROBST: Oh!
Dre's is in and out for Moto.
Yau-Man needs to score to keep
Ravu in it.
Very close.
Moto could win it with this
shot.
Just short.
Yau-Man launches for Ravu.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Close again.
Dre rims it.
Ravu can stay alive.
Yau-Man just misses.
Dre scores for Moto!
Moto wins reward!
Moto, congratulations.
You continue to dominate,
undefeated in challenges thus
far.
Which of the three rewards are
you going to take?
>> The fishing gear.
>> PROBST: Fishing gear.
Which tribe member of Ravu's
are you going to send to Exile
Island?
>> Sylvia.
>> PROBST: Sylvia.
>> I was afraid of that.
>> PROBST: Sylvia, grab your
bag.
Boat's waiting.
>> Bye, sweetie.
>> Good luck. Sorry.
>> PROBST: Moto, more riches.
Come get your reward, head back
to camp.
>> Today at challenge, I didn't
do very well, and I'm very
embarrassed by it.
This is the second time I've
been separated from my tribe in
only seven days, and they're
probably sitting around and
saying, "We should've let Sylvia
go sooner 'cause she's a real
albatross around our neck."
Clue number three: "When night
has fallen and the tribe is
asleep, you'll find it under the
cave's threshold if you dig
deep."
Interesting.
The third clue is so helpful.
It said, dig right under the
tallest part of the arch of the
cave, and the immunity idol
will be there.
I'm in a... probably the most
tenuous position right now with
my tribe.
The idol is right smack-dab in
the middle of camp, so I need to
figure out a time and a place to
look for the idol as quickly as
possible.
>> SEVERAL (chanting): Moto!
Moto! Moto!
(whooping)
>> Oh, man, we are eating good.
>> Oh, yeah, baby!
>> We take no prisoners, not
even women and the children.
>> I loved that challenge,
seeing people slip and fall.
>> I am so happy we got this.
>> And as long as we keep the
lead, our morale stays up,
their morale goes down-- bam,
there it is right there, that
whole game, every time.
So funny when Papa Smurf
fell down.
(laughter)
>> That was funny.
>> When he fell down, I was,
like, "Golly!"
>> Who?
>> Papa Smurf.
>> I've busted ribs before, and
it feels like I... just like
when I broke that one, can't get
a deep breath.
Just... had some dizziness, uh,
before, where I kind of just...
and it feels like it's the same
thing.
>> We were all sitting around,
and all of a sudden, you know,
we noticed Gary wasn't doing
too well.
He took a pretty hard fall in
the challenge, so, you know, we
were just concerned.
So we got the medics to come out
here and take a look at him.
>> Is it hard for you to talk?
>> No, no.
>> Yeah... okay.
>> And that's... I don't know...
>> He was afraid.
He said he didn't want to die
in Fiji.
And that he was real afraid.
He couldn't-- he didn't know
where he was.
I know this is a passion for
him.
A lot of people look at it as a
game, but he's older.
And I just want him to be okay.
>> Yeah.
>> See if that helps you.
>> Okay.
>> Will that be all right?
>> Yes.
>> All righty?
>> The plan for now is to have
Gary just rest for a while, see
how he wakes up in the morning.
>> Thank you.
>> Take care.
>> But my thinking is if he
cannot breathe, you know,
it's...
It's best for him to just go
and get that taken care of.
>> Yeah.
>> Gary's a great guy.
I mean, we all kind of look up
to the guy, and, you know, he's
in our prayers, and we just
hope he gets better.
>> Tree mail!
Come and get it!
>> We've got mail?
>> Yep.
>> "Keeping your tribe together
won't require brawn.
This one is a true test of
will, and now it's time to get
it on."
>> A physical one.
>> No, it won't require brawn.
It's endurance.
>> Today, we're getting ready
for another challenge.
Don't know what it entails.
It's kind of hard to speculate
because, in this game, when you
think it's going one way, all
of a sudden, it goes the other.
>> Gary showing up to the next
challenge in this sort of
weakened position is going to
hurt our tribe, so if it's
going to be the case that he's
just not going to be able to
perform, then it's in his best
interest, as well as ours, to
just-- he should just call it
quits.
We're going to keep a close eye
on him, and, you know, if
anything happens, his health is
more important than the game to
us.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Sylvia,
returning from Exile Island.
First things first.
Edgardo, bring me the immunity
idol, please.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
compete head-to-head in a
food-eating competition.
Ravu very excited to have food.
>> We're hungry!
We're a lot hungrier than those
guys, there.
>> PROBST: First tribe member
to get their food down scores a
point for their tribe.
First tribe to four wins
immunity, guaranteed at least
another day out here in Fiji.
Losers, Tribal Council tonight,
somebody will be going home.
First round, Liliana for Moto
taking on Rocky from Ravu.
I can assure you, everything
you're going to eat today
Fijians eat.
First round is giant clams.
(everyone groaning)
>> PROBST: Eat it however you
can get it down.
When you're done, show me an
empty mouth.
If there's still something in
there, I'll let you know.
If you're good, I'll say you
win.
Three, two, one, eat.
Rocky shoves it down his mouth.
Trying to swallow it.
Liliana taking her time and
chewing.
That's a lot of giant clam.
No, you're not done.
A little bit in the teeth.
No, Rocky!
For Ravu.
Liliana, you still got it
hanging down.
Ravu leads one-zip.
Just so we're clear, when I say
empty mouth, it's got to be
empty.
If you got stuff hanging down,
it's not empty.
Next round is Sylvia for Ravu
taking on Dreamz for Moto.
>> Sylvia, you're hungry.
>> PROBST: Octopus.
You will each eat one octopus
tentacle.
Ready?
Three, two, one, eat.
Those are big tentacles.
Dreamz's chewing that like a
piece of beef jerky.
Sylvia's torn hers all apart
into bite-size.
>> Attagirl!
Let's go!
>> PROBST: We are very close
once again.
Sylvia getting a lot of hers
down.
Very close.
Got to show me a completely
empty mouth.
Who can swallow fastest?
Sylvia got a little nub on
there.
Don't lose it.
Dre has it for Moto!
We are tied one-one.
Next round is Lisi taking on
Mookie.
Peanut worms.
Moto leads two-one.
You're playing to five.
Three, two, one, eat.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Mookie digging in,
chewing on those peanut worms.
Lisi off to a slower start.
>> Yeah!
Chew it up!
>> PROBST: Mookie not messing
around.
Lisi is in trouble.
Not looking good for Moto on
this one.
>> Come on, Mook.
Come on!
>> You're good.
One more, baby, one more!
>> PROBST: Mookie taunting
Lisi, trying to get her to
vomit.
Trying to get her to throw up.
Mookie very close for Ravu.
>> Show me the money, Mook!
Show me the money, Mook.
>> PROBST: Mookie has it for
Ravu!
Ravu leads two-one.
>> Was it nasty?
>> It was nasty.
>> PROBST: You didn't like the
taunting?
>> Well, no, not at all.
I mean, that-- that might have
just have stopped our goodwill
towards them.
Goodwill and sportsmanship is
to be humble.
>> You guys taunt, too, bro.
It's not one-sided brother.
>> We don't taunt, and we still
wish all the best of luck.
>> I wish you the best of
luck too, but it's all fair in
love and war, baby.
Chill out; relax.
You blow off two people and
then tell me how you feel, bro.
>> PROBST: Ready to keep going?
>> Yeah.
>> Please.
>> PROBST: It's going to be
Earl for Ravu taking on Alex
for Moto.
Sea cucumber.
>> Easy, bro.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one, go.
Earl can't even hold on to his,
he's so excited to eat.
>> All right, Alex, come on.
Come on!
>> Come on, Alex!
Come on, Alex!
>> PROBST: Alex working on his
second piece of sea cucumber.
Earl still working on his first.
>> Come on, Earl!
You're behind, baby!
Come on.
>> PROBST: Alex now on his
third and final piece of sea
cucumber.
>> Swallow it!
Swallow it!
>> PROBST: Earl, it's mind over
matter.
>> Come on!
>> Come on, Earl.
Come on, come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Does he have it?
Alex has it for Moto!
We are tied two-two.
>> No water... no water...
>> It wouldn't go down?
>> Yeah-- no water.
>> PROBST: Next round is
Michelle for Ravu taking on
Edgardo for Moto.
Fish eyes.
>> Nice, Michelle.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one.
Eat.
Edgardo just swallowing, not
even messing around.
Michelle quickly falling behind.
>> Come on, Michelle!
Come on, Michelle!
>> Go, Michelle.
>> PROBST: Edgardo has it for
Moto!
Moto leads three-two.
>> Yes!
>> That's okay, Michelle.
That's all right, baby.
>> PROBST: This could be the
last round.
It's going to be Papa Smurf
for Moto, taking on Anthony for
Ravu.
A lot on the line.
Gary, you could win immunity
again for Moto.
Anthony, fate is in your hands.
You have to win or you guys are
going to Tribal Council tonight.
Let's see how you do with pig
snouts.
Still a little hair on the
snout.
>> Come on, baby!
>> Bacon, baby, bacon.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one, eat.
>> Come on, Papa!
>> Papa Smurf!
>> Papa.
>> Let's go, Anthony!
>> PROBST: Gary like he's
done it every day of his life.
Hammering that snout down.
Anthony struggling to get it
down.
>> Hey, you don't got to chew
all of it.
You don't got to chew all of it.
Just swallow, baby.
>> We're behind, baby, come on!
Chew fast!
>> PROBST: Papa Smurf starting
on his second snout.
>> Come on, Papa Smurf.
>> PROBST: Anthony has really
slowed down his chewing.
>> Come on Anthony!
>> TEAM (chanting): Papa Smurf!
>> PROBST: Gary puts down the
the last bite.
Anthony still struggling with
that first bite.
>> TEAM: Papa Smurf! Papa Smurf!
Papa Smurf!
>> PROBST: Moto wins immunity
again!
Moto remains undefeated so far
in this game.
Ravu, still winless, more bad
news, Tribal Council tonight.
Another member of your tribe
going home.
Grab your bags, head back to
camp.
See you at Tribal.
(squawking, chittering)
>> (yells)
We lost again.
>> That was a tough challenge.
Hey.
>> Four times in a row is hard.
What are you gonna do?
>> I just want to let you guys
know I was absolutely mortified
yesterday by my performance,
okay?
I just wanted to say I'm really
sorry that I let the team down
on that one challenge.
>> If, at the moment, that was
the best you can do, then...
>> Okay, thanks for letting me
get it off my chest.
(indistinct chatter)
I don't know if the tribe is
still connected to me.
I certainly still feel connected
to the tribe.
But I was gone for almost 24
hours, and... I've been a target
since first day.
Because I'm definitely the
oldest woman, and the least
amount of strength, probably the
least amount of skills.
It is absolutely essential that
I find the idol before Tribal
Council, or else I will be the
next one voted off.
>> She's trying a bit too hard.
>> I'm right there with you.
I'm just trying to keep my butt
in the game.
I'm trying not to scramble
around too much.
I think that Sylvia's getting
voted out tonight.
Probably the most interesting
complication that can happen
during Tribal Council will be if
Sylvia actually has the idol.
And if she breaks it out, it's
gonna change up some...
everything.
Because whoever she picks...
goes home.
>> So, let's run over what we're
gonna do tonight, huh?
>> Um...
>> Sylvia's... Basically, the
majority, uh, is gonna vote for
Sylvia on this one, all right?
>> Okay. Mm-hmm.
>> And then, to back it up, just
in case she does have the idol--
'cause, you know, she's playing
off like she doesn't, but not a
big deal-- we'll put Anthony's
name in there, too, 'cause we...
>> So we have a backup.
>> Yeah. Cool?
>> Sounds like a plan.
>> Ready, break?
Ready, break. All right.
>> James approached me and said
that the plan was that Sylvia
was gonna be voted out unless
she had the immunity idol, and,
then, in which case, we would be
voting, uh, Anthony out.
>> Does he irk you at all, or
no?
Yeah.
He just seems like a... like
a... like a... a little on the
whiny side, you know?
>> Well, like, he's so
wishy-washy.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't want to vote out
either Sylvia or Anthony.
We've made our voting decisions,
supposedly, to try to make the
tribe stronger, but the
reality is that it hasn't.
So I'm gonna do something that's
not "with the tribe."
>> Anthony, he's... he's the
most, you know...
I don't know what's going on in
his mind.
And especially today, when
someone puts a gun to your head,
"Finish this in a minute."
I don't care if you have no
water in your mouth, you're
going to finish it.
He was still on the same little
bit, and then he's, like,
complaining about it.
>> That bothered you, huh?
>> This bit!
Anthony just... I was not happy
at all with his performance in
the challenge.
He's just not that strong, and I
think it's just the effort that
he put forward that just really
irritated me.
So, uh...
>> Mm-hmm?
>> Where's Anthony?
>> Not around.
>> So you're good with that,
Sylvia?
>> Mm-hmm, yeah.
>> Okay.
>> I'm good.
I'm not sure how it's going to
go tonight.
I mean, I hear, supposedly, that
majority is going to vote for
Anthony, but I'm not feeling
really absolutely certain.
I am pretty sure I know where
the idol is.
From the three clues that have
been given out so far, it seems
to me that it's going to be at
the threshold of the tallest
point of the cave.
So I still have a little bit of
time before Tribal Council, and
I'm going to dig right now and
try to get that idol as my
insurance policy.
If I get the idol now, and if
the vote does go my way, I will
be able to surprise everybody.
>> PROBST: Let's start with a
quick poll, one word answers.
What is the state of the tribe?
Anthony.
>> Tired.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man.
>> Not very happy.
>> PROBST: Michelle.
>> Hungry.
>> PROBST: Rocky.
>> Tired.
>> PROBST: Mookie.
>> Bad.
>> PROBST: I'm watching a group
of people that are
disintegrating, emotionally,
before my eyes.
Mookie, what needs to happen
with this tribe?
The game is slipping through
your fingers.
>> We need to come through in a
challenge.
Uh, I think the more we lose,
the idea the rich get richer,
the poor get poorer, comes
to seep into our minds, and,
uh, it's starting to mess with
us, definitely.
>> PROBST: Sylvia, you struggled
in the reward challenge.
>> I did.
I mean, I was just mortified for
disappointing the tribe, for not
getting that one more basket in.
The second thing was a little
bit of self-performance here:
why are you not able to do the
clutch move when you need to do
it?
>> PROBST: Anthony, today, you
squared off against Gary-- Papa
Smurf.
The head-to-head between you two
guys was over before it started.
>> I was just trying to swallow,
and I had no spit to swallow.
You know, I was out here in the
tropics chewing pig snout and
enjoying it.
I just couldn't swallow it.
>> PROBST: Rocky, trust.
Does it start to become even
more difficult, when you lose
time after time after time,
to trust people?
>> I think it becomes more
important.
You have to trust that there is
a possibility that one day you
are going to snap out of this
and you're going to start
winning.
If you lose that, you might as
well just not even show up to
the game.
>> PROBST: Anthony, Mookie
trustworthy?
>> I think Mookie is pretty
trustworthy.
I'm generally the person who,
for the most part, gives people
the benefit of the doubt.
>> PROBST: The problem with that
is, by the time you figure out
you can't trust him, it could be
as you're walking out of here.
>> You know, I often wonder
if the... if these folks even
like me.
I think... I like to think they
like me, but you know, sometimes
you can't tell.
>> PROBST: Mookie, what's your
thought on what Anthony said?
>> To be honest, after the
challenge, I was really pissed
off.
And one person that just brought
me over the top was Anthony.
I understand that it's hard to
swallow, but when you take a
little piece of snout this
small, you can will yourself to
throw it down.
>> PROBST: Anthony, he's not
only saying you didn't have
enough effort today, he's
questioning your will to win.
>> I have the will to win.
I have the will to be here.
I have the will to keep going
through this game.
I'm out there in the same stuff
with you, dude.
I guess I pissed you off.
Okay, fine.
But, you know, you want to
question my will...
>> I don't... I don't want to
make it personal.
The thing is...
>> Well, you know, it's gonna
be personal.
>> Not everyone was able to put
it down.
>> Well, apparently I'm the only
one who put you over the top.
>> PROBST: One last topic to
talk about: hidden immunity
idol.
Earl's been out there once,
Sylvia twice.
What was the mood back at camp
today, Rocky, knowing she had
three clues?
Were you trying to figure out if
she had the idol or not?
>> Of course we are.
She could be holding it in her
back pocket right now.
I don't know.
>> PROBST: Okay, if somebody
does indeed have the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, you would play it after
the votes have been cast, before
I read them.
It is time to vote.
Mookie, you're up.
>> It's not your will.
It's your attitude.
>> I just got to know if you
have the idol or not.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: If you have the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now is the time
to do so.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
First vote, Sylvia.
Anthony.
Sylvia.
Two votes Sylvia, one vote
Anthony.
Anthony-- two votes Anthony.
Sylvia-- three votes Sylvia.
Anthony.
We're tied: three votes
Anthony, three votes Sylvia.
Earl.
That's one vote Earl, three
votes Anthony, three votes
Sylvia, one vote left.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji... Sylvia.
You need to bring me your torch.
Sylvia, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Well, one good thing
that came out of tonight's
Tribal Council: a little
honesty.
Maybe it will make a difference.
Grab your torches.
Go back to camp.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I just can't... I can't
function.
>> PROBST: Gary breaks down.
>> His head spinning is just
getting worse.
>> If he doesn't get better,
he's going to have to go.
>> PROBST: Liliana makes a move
on the guys.
(laughing)
And Anthony takes a beating.
>> You get all sentimental and
sensitive.
>> There's no way in hell I'm
gonna give it up.
>> So I've been had, and, um,
I'm not too happy about it.
Um, I actually really, really
liked the entire group of both
tribes because we had three days
to get to know everybody, and
I'm not that angry or resentful
right now.
I'm just looking forward to
seeing them all after they've
clawed each other's eyes out
later on.