>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Yau-Man discovered the Immunity
Idol hidden at Moto...
>> This is my million dollars.
Mwah!
>> PROBST: ...and he immediately
informed Earl.
>> I would have never thought
that a big, strong black man
would become one of my best
allies.
>> PROBST: At Ravu, Mookie, Alex
and Edgardo found the idol
hidden at their camp.
They made a pact not to tell
Lisi or Dreamz.
>> Dreamz is not so good about
keeping his trap shut, so we're
doing it for his protection and
our own.
>> PROBST: Lisi had no idea that
the idol had been found.
>> A little idol digging?
I'm, like, "Dude, you're gonna
have to wake up really, really
early to fool an old cat like
me.
What's wrong with you?"
>> PROBST: At the Reward
Challenge, the Survivors squared
off in a dance competition...
>> Okay!
>> PROBST: ...and Earl led Moto
to victory.
>> Moto.
(cheering, shouting)
>> All right, then.
>> PROBST: Lisi was banished to
Exile Island, where she broke
down.
>> I really don't want to be
here, but what am I supposed to
do, man?
(thunder crashing)
I feel like quitting.
>> PROBST: At the Immunity
Challenge...
(cheering)
...Yau-Man dominated for Moto.
Moto wins immunity!
>> Flex my muscle!
>> PROBST: With another Tribal
Council looming, it looked like
Ravu's decision was clear.
>> I don't see you guys winning
the next Reward Challenge, and
that means I get to go to Exile
Island again.
>> PROBST: When Lisi threw in
the towel...
>> I'm done like a Thanksgiving
Day turkey, man.
(clucks like a turkey)
>> The fact that Lisi wants to
quit pissed me off, because I
could probably use her in the
future.
>> PROBST: But Lisi had second
thoughts...
>> What would happen if... we
kept on going?
>> PROBST: ...which threw
Edgardo and Alex for a loop.
At Tribal Council...
>> I think Lisi wants to go
home.
>> PROBST: ...Dreamz called Lisi
out.
>> Do you want to be here?
>> Okay...
>> It's a yes or no question,
Lisi.
>> Well, I have to think for a
minute, I have to just chill...
>> Jeff, I'm ready to vote.
>> PROBST: In the end, Lisi's
indecisiveness got her
unanimously voted off.
Lisi, the tribe has spoken.
Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(sizzling)
>> Do you have the idol now
with you?
Hey, put it here, man.
Are you sure?
>> Yeah.
>> And if you use it against
me, I'm gonna ... you over,
man.
>> Okay.
The idol I have in my pocket is
actually for...
You know, I'm selfish.
I'll admit it in this game.
It's for myself, to get myself
further along in this game.
Now, if that plays into my
alliance with these guys, to use
these guys to get further, then
I'll, you know, I'm all for it.
>> We're placing our faith in
you, man.
Okay, fair enough.
>> Dreamz, hey, man.
>> Edgardo, Mookie and myself
have not told Dreamz about the
Immunity Idol.
Not because we want to keep it
from him so that we can use it
against him, but really, it's
just because we don't think
Dreamz is good about keeping
information to himself.
>> Not bad at all.
>> I know, but one at a time,
you know?
>> Tree Mail!
>> It's not a good Tree Mail.
>> Uh-oh.
>> "Gather your personal
belongings only, and use the map
to paddle your tribe boat to
Exile Island immediately.
You are not allowed to bring
rewards, tools or flints.
Bring only your personal items,
including your canteen."
>> We need to boil up the rest
of that rice.
>> Boil it up, boil it up.
>> Boil it up.
>> Are we living on Exile
Island for the rest of the time?
We got Tree Mail, and we're
like, "Oh, man, we're leaving
our camp."
You know, this sucks.
>> Nope.
>> The fact that I've been
through, you know, the old Ravu
situation, I know I can sleep
in the dirt and not eat a lot
of food for a while.
Me and Earl actually exchanged
places, and we were like, "This
is great.
We can totally do this."
Cassandra, Stacy and Boo have
been living the whole time on
Honeymoon Fiji here, and they're
like, "Oh, my God, we're gonna
die."
>> Gather round, horsemen.
Let's see what we've got.
>> Is this mail?
>> This is a map.
>> It's a map.
>> Oh!
>> "Gather your personal
belongings only, and use this
map to paddle your tribe boat
to Exile Island immediately.
You're not allowed to bring
rewards, tools or flints.
Bring only your personal items,
including your canteens."
>> Sounds like we're about to
mix and match again.
>> No, we... we all go to Exile
Island.
That's where we stay now.
We all merge at Exile Island.
What do you think about that?
>> We're ready.
>> I think we're merging.
>> All right, guys, um, so, all
right, let's do it, man.
>> Let's do it.
>> I don't know what to expect
right now.
The game takes so many twists.
I'm hoping for a merge, but if
it's not, I mean, it's part of
the game.
>> All right, so we need to be
clear on who we're targeting.
We're targeting Cassandra.
>> I'm getting Cassandra.
>> You're Michelle?
Let's target Stacy.
>> So the master plan is
basically, if we merge, Dreamz
tries to pull Cassandra over,
giving us five-five, Mookie
tries to pull Michelle or
Yau-Man, and I think I can pull
Stacy.
>> Remember this time right
here.
Remember how we felt when we was
Ain't nobody gonna turn back,
you know what I'm saying?
>> And the bottom line is, each
of us has proven our loyalty to
the other by essentially giving
up someone we were aligned with
for the sake of the four, the
four horsemen.
You gave up Rock.
We gave up Lisi.
Right now, we have to get nasty,
and we have to use everything
that we have.
>> Yeah.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Everybody's a bit nervous.
Uh, we don't know if a merge is
coming up or how it's going to
work.
People pretty much wracked their
brains trying to figure out
what's going to happen next, and
I think that everybody is
depending on this merge because
they're nervous.
>> They're coming.
They're right there.
>> So you get dependent on
something.
"Well, I know I'm going to be
safe once I get my boys back."
But hey, there might not be a
merge.
I mean, you just never know.
What took you so long?
Instead of thinking so far ahead
about this merge and depending
on that...
Back again.
...you better think about right
now who's watching you and might
want to vote you off tomorrow.
>> When we got to Exile Island
and we met up with each other,
we greeted each other.
>> Hey, Yau, how you doing?
>> Hi, baby!
>> And some of us thought a
merge is happening.
Others thought that there's a
big party waiting for us
somewhere.
Uh, we still have our own colors
and our own flags with us, so
we have no idea what's going on.
>> Where are we going here?
Are we going in there?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's check it out.
>> Here we go again.
>> When we got to Exile Island,
there was no instruction.
Jeff wasn't around.
Um, I thought we were just kind
of going to live on Exile
Island.
We assumed maybe all ten of us
were going to live there and
it's going to suck, but hey, at
least we came from Ravu, where
it kind of sucks anyway, so
whatever.
(Cassandra sighs)
>> We decided to go to the top
of the tower to see if there was
Tree Mail.
The entire tribe made it up
together.
We got into our own little tree
house, expecting that this was
where we were going to be for a
while.
>> Fishing is how to do it.
>> What the hell, then?
>> Is this the cannibalism part?
>> Look at that!
>> Oh, wow.
>> New colors!
New buffs.
>> Finally, I get rid of the
orange.
>> No orange.
>> All right, everyone got their
buffs?
>> "Congratulations, you have
made it far and now merged into
one tribe.
Drop your old buffs and wear
these new ones with pride as
you paddle in one boat to your
home, the old Moto camp."
( cheering )
>> I get to see Moto!
For once, I get to see Moto and
experience that island because
I am the only person that has
not been there yet.
So we're all going to be back
there.
>> I'm so elated to be going
back to Moto.
I was thinking, "Oh, Lord, how
am I going to make it on Exile
Island?
We're going to be with snakes,
and no bed, no couch.
Lord, please, what are we going
to do?"
So, um, oh, my God, I am so
elated.
>> Whoo!
>> All right!
>> Thank God, after seven days
of hell at Ravu, I get to eat
rice, potatoes, a toothbrush,
toothpaste, a shower, and I
smell like crap, I know.
I'll probably get a turn
turn at the bed tonight.
Finally, finally, things are
looking up.
>> Let's see if we have
surprises.
>> See if we have a flag,
a new name.
>> Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
>> I can't even get a bed?!
>> They took everything.
>> I didn't, I didn't get
anything.
>> Fishing gear.
>> Oh, what the hell?!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, no!
This is, like, a bad dream.
>> This is, like, this is so
messed up.
Oh, my God!
>> Bastards!
>> Oh, my God!
>> This is so not cool.
>> This is real Survivor.
We have a cave.
>> We got a pot and a machete.
>> We have a pot, machete and a
we got a cave.
>> And that's it.
That's all we need.
>> We've already been trained
for this.
>> When we got on to the Moto
beach, turned the corner, and lo
and behold, nothing.
I mean nothing.
We got a little bit of fishing
gear, a couple of pots, a
machete, a flint, and that's it.
>> I've never seen Moto.
>> You never did get to see
Moto, did you?
>> Never got a bed.
I never a toothbrush.
I never got anything.
>> Everything was gone.
No bed, no couch, no shelter,
no bathroom, no nothing.
I felt okay with that.
I kind of laughed.
Had a little smirk on my face
because I've already been
trained.
You know, being at the old Ravu
for 13 days-- hey, I'm just back
home again.
>> Everybody has the same way
now, so.
>> Good.
>> All right, well...
>> Everybody gather around for
the mail.
All right.
"Now it is time to reveal your
world from scratch.
Give yourself a new name, paint
your new flag, and start the
game anew."
>> That's it?
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> Let's do it.
>> All right.
>> Okay, what's the name, guys?
>> Something that has to do
with the islands or something
I don't know.
>> Venaca.
>> Isn't Venaca "thank you"?
>> Thank you.
>> And "Bula" is hello.
>> Let's do Bula.
>> Bula-Bula.
>> I... I vote for that.
>> Bula-Bula it is.
>> Bula-Bula.
>> Either that, either that or
the nooky-nooky tribe.
>> Bula-nooky.
>> Bula-looky-nooky.
>> Hello.
>> So who's good, who's good at
drawing?
>> Me and Stacy?
>> We decided on Bula-Bula as
the tribe name because "Bula"
is how you say "hello" in Fiji.
>> On the flag itself or on
what-what's going on here?
>> The flag.
>> No, I wanted to look at our
canvas.
We can never be so sure in this
game, you know.
>> I know.
>> We want to be in a safe spot.
I think we are now, don't you?
>> Yeah, yeah.
I'm a little worried because you
guys are all still super close.
>> Yeah, but the thing is,
Michelle, is that I don't that
think that we're a threat
because we're girls, and those
guys are going to get super
competitive.
It's interesting, I think boys
are going to start attacking
boys and getting them off game
before they're going to touch
the girls, because they look at
us as non-threats.
So we'll be, like, the last to
go.
I mean that's how it's lined up
for now.
We're in a pretty good spot.
>> Now I'm like-- now I'm
thinking like the other island
is better.
>> As far as fishing, yeah.
>> Because we could get more
food.
>> Like crabs.
We're a new tribe now.
But there-there's a core group.
There's a tribe within the tribe
and the tribe within the tribe
is myself, Michelle, Cassandra,
and Yau.
Now it's just divide and
conquer.
We have to kind of divide up
that old Moto and get them one
by one and knock them out.
>> What do you all want to do?
>> Yeah, let's divide everything
up and just get-get going.
So the moment has final arrived.
These first couple of hours are
really crucial.
They're going to determine who's
the final five.
I'm ready to fight.
>> All right, so who's going to
go fishing?
>> I can go.
>> I'll go.
>> Let's go us four, then.
>> There are two slings.
Two people can be crabbing while
another couple of people can sit
on the boat and try to fish.
>> I had my niche in the first
Moto tribe.
I had my niche in the second
Moto tribe and I was very
comfortable.
At this point, I'm not
comfortable at all, so I'm
going-going to take a backseat.
And that's all I can do is be a
good little helper, and then
when it's time, I'll assume
leadership role again.
>> How was camp over here?
>> It was good.
It was nice.
We had a good little, um, thing
going.
>> Me and Dreamz hooked up at
Ravu, so we got good.
>> I was hoping that.
I was hoping that.
>> Yeah, I mean we clicked and
then... he said, you and I saw--
I said, you know me and Yau,
like I trust Yau at Ravu.
>> And Earl and Michelle.
>> Am I still one who trusts
someone, Yau?
>> Yeah.
>> Or have I left?
>> No, I didn't go to the dark
side.
>> We were all afraid.
>> First second, we got onto
this island, four horsemen as
we discussed-- we were going to
go split up and figure out what
was happening at Moto.
And so we went straight to work,
and infiltrated that group and
kind of gained their trust.
>> Are you guys good with Boo?
Do you guys like him or...?
>> Oh, no.
I'm a...
>> He goes first.
>> We can't decide whether it's
Boo or Stacy.
Stacy because we don't want the
Alex connection, but now that
we merged...
Yeah.
>> And that's the thing, Boo
just stirs up too much...
>> He gets it going quick.
>> Yeah, he stirs too much.
You gotta get him out before he
starts, like...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Right away, we found they
want Boo out, and then we take
out Stacy.
Right now, our plan is working
out perfectly as far as what we
know.
We just have to execute it
right.
>> So, Boo first?
>> Boo first.
And then Stacy or Alex.
>> Currently, I'm the only one
with the idol, and Earl is the
only one who knows I have the
idol.
Potentially, there should be two
immunity idols in play right now
in the game.
The question is who's got the
other one?
The next opportunity we have we
would like to vote out Boo, and
I think we have pretty much
secure Mookie's and Dreamz's
votes, but we don't trust nobody
here.
>> Oh, it's so cute!
>> There you go!
>> Yeah, he goes first.
For sure.
>> I really have a lot of trust
in Alex, because we're both
original Moto, and that's just,
you know, the chance that I'm
taking.
But he's the most trustworthy
person that I can think of right
now.
>> I mean, I think we should do
what's most convenient for us.
You know, me, you, and Ed are
tighter-- are going to be
tighter together than whoever
it is that's around.
>> And then we-we also are more
solid, too, on a vote.
>> Yeah, we're more solid...
>> Against two.
>> I can use the relationships
I've had to sort of create smoke
and mirrors, to keep them sort
of guessing, so that, you know,
the four horsemen can take it
all the way.
Unless I'm mistaken, the four of
us are controlling this game
right now.
I could be wrong, and I could
be getting set up, but this is
my best bet.
What can I do?
I know you're smart.
I'm not worried about you.
I just wanted you have all the
information I have.
>> No, I appreciate it.
>> We all want Boo off.
>> Yeah, so Boo's going to go
off first.
>> And then we're going to get
Stacy off second.
>> The thing is-- yeah...
>> Okay.
>> All of a sudden, Mookie let
Dreamz know that we had the
idol, and as soon as that
happened, my gut was like, "Ooh,
that was not so smart."
But you can't say a ... word.
>> You can't say...
>> Do I look like...? Shut up.
>> No, no, no, no, just...
>> I'm not... no, I'm not...
>> Don't tell, don't tell
Cassandra.
>> When Alex and Mookie told me
that they had the immunity idol,
I was kind of mad because they
didn't tell me when they first
found it.
>> Just a few days ago.
>> Why didn't y'all tell me?
>> 'Cause we didn't...
>> Only because of Cassandra,
just to make sure.
But we were going to tell you.
>> We had a pact, and they kind
of made me not trust them a
little bit and-and made me feel
that I was on the outskirts.
So, point-blank, I'm going to
trust them until I can't trust
them no more.
Strange.
No, I wouldn't have said
anything.
I'm glad you all told me now
because I was getting kind of
scared.
I-I was getting kind of scared
about...
>> ...now it works perfect.
>> Now is everything's perfect.
Let's do it, y'all.
Don't screw up.
No more talk.
>> Dreamz knows about the
immunity idol, by the way.
>> Who told him?
>> Mookie wanted to tell him.
>> You told Dreamz about the
idol, man?
>> Why?
>> All right, I'm going to tell
you right now, I don't like that
plan.
Like not-not that I don't trust
you, but trusting all these
people...
>> No, no, either way, we're
taking out Boo first.
That's-that's everyone's
consensus.
>> I'm pissed off about the
whole situation right now.
We found the immunity idol.
It's something that, you know,
you need to keep between three
or two people to make it work.
That's all the people that
needed to be told, and Mookie
just told Dreamz out of nowhere.
And now I feel really
uncomfortable because Dreamz
has the... knows about the idol;
Cassandra knows about the idol;
Earl knows about the idol.
>> Do you get what I'm saying?
>> Maybe-- I mean, I don't know
how you feel about this, but we
should maybe just take Boo out
first, and then at that point
Stacy has nowhere to go.
And I trust Stacy.
She's not gonna, she's not
gonna...
So we could pull her in.
That's five.
That's a five-four majority.
That's the simplest way.
Stacy will be loyal, and we
don't really have to worry
about her winning the final
immunity, I don't think.
And we can put whatever order
you want.
I don't care.
>> I mean, that's fine.
The original plan was to
actually take out Boo and then
Stacy.
Things changed.
Alex and Edgardo want to bring
Stacy.
Now, bringing on Stacy is only
in their best interest, because
they still have the
relationship from the old Moto.
So when it gets down to five,
as we planned, Stacy is on
their side, and me and Dreamz,
you know, we're left out of the
loop.
>> If Dreamz tells somebody,
I'm going to kill you, Mookie,
man, seriously.
>> No one knows who has who.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And that's great.
(chuckles)
>> You're still the most
popular girl here right now.
You and Michelle, too, actually.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Michelle's getting pretty
popular.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And long as they just,
they don't pay any attention to
Dreamz still.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I don't think, I still don't
trust Mookie.
>> Uh-huh.
My alliance is with some of the
people from Ravu side: Earl,
Yau-Man.
And then Earl has Michelle on
his side, and then definitely
Dreamz.
I was really hoping that he
would make it through to the
merge.
We've pretty much got the
numbers on our side.
>> Hey, just keep them thinking
that they have you.
Keep them thinking that I'm not
thinking.
>> Mm-hmm.
Yes, I'll definitely do that.
That's easy.
>> We'll just sail on.
I was actually happy about the
merge 'cause now the game is
really on.
It's time to take it to the
advanced level.
>> Let's see what's going on
there.
>> I'm like, do I bring my shoes
or do I run?
>> What?
>> Still Boo?
>> Boo, Stacy-- 'cause that's
two out of the way.
>> What they're saying now is
they want to keep Stacy on
board and use her the whole
time to have majority.
>> That's me and you out.
>> I know, I know, I know.
That's why I don't want to take
Stacy with us.
>> No way, no, point blank, no.
>> They just want Stacy on
their side to take one of us
off.
>> Take one of us off.
>> Because we said guaranteed
five.
>> Yeah.
>> Take one of us out, then
he's gonna take us out.
That will bring too much into
Alex's hands.
>> I ain't trusting nobody with
Stacy around, you know what I
mean?
'Cause they gonna always have
numbers with Stacy around.
That's why I said Stacy second.
Do you understand?
I was planning a long time ago.
I'm really looking forward to
voting off Stacy because she
treated me so bad when I was
with the old Moto.
She treated Cassandra so bad,
and all of a sudden she's happy
and nice and glad to see me all
of a sudden 'cause I got
friends and she ain't got the
power no more.
She's got to go.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
I'll take that from you, Earl.
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Draw a stone.
Do not look at it in your hand.
Separate bag for the ladies.
Keep it covered.
One left for you, Earl.
Everybody, put your hands out.
Everybody, reveal.
If you have orange, go to the
orange mat.
If you have green, go to the
green mat.
>> Another twist.
>> PROBST: Edgardo, you kind of
shrugged your shoulders.
>> I don't know what to expect
anymore.
I'm just like, well, you know,
bring it on.
Let's do it.
Let's do this right now.
>> PROBST: Boo, what do you
think's happening?
>> I think we've switched again.
>> PROBST: You have merged.
You are one tribe, but for
today's challenge, you will be
competing against each other.
You are two teams in this
challenge.
The green team will be Alex,
Michelle, Mookie, Stacy, and
Dreamz.
And the orange team: Edgardo,
Cassandra, Boo, Yau-Man and
Earl.
All right, should I tell you
about the challenge?
>> Yes, please.
>> PROBST: On my go, you will be
shown a large Fijian mask and
given time to memorize the
symbols and their arrangement on
the mask.
You will then paddle in your
boat down the river to three
different stations.
Each time you come to a
station, you must retrieve a
bundle of puzzle pieces.
When you have all three
bundles, you'll paddle to the
finish.
Two tribe members from each
team will then use those pieces
to construct six of the symbols
that you saw on that mask.
You must then place the symbols
in the correct order on your
team mask.
First team to get it right wins.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Winning team wins
immunity.
The five people on that team
will not go to Tribal Council.
You will be safe from another
vote and guaranteed a
one-in-nine shot at a million
bucks.
In addition, the winning team
will feast.
Steak, skillet to cook it in,
some seasoning, vegetables,
couple bottles of wine.
Worth playing for?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: For the losers,
nothing except this note and a
date with me at Tribal Council.
All right.
We'll get you guys in your
boats, we'll get started.
Here we go.
Reveal the mask.
The symbols you want to study
are the symbols in the turtle
shell at the top of the mask.
Whenever you're ready, take off.
This challenge has begun.
>> Ready.
>> PROBST: Green team thinks
they have it.
They're heading out first.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Yau-Man says they've got it
for the orange.
Both teams are paddling.
>> Turn, turn, turn.
>> Turn, turn, turn to the
right, turn to the right, guys.
>> Turn to the right!
>> PROBST: Both teams at the
first station.
>> Okay, stop.
>> PROBST: Stacy trying to get
her bundle of pieces off.
There is a learning curve
here...
>> Back up.
>> PROBST: ...how to use this
tool.
>> Just keep it steady.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man has a system.
He's working it.
>> Switch out real quick.
>> Yeah, go ahead, go ahead.
>> PROBST: Stacy having trouble.
They're gonna switch out.
Dreamz gonna get up there now
and give it a shot.
Yau-Man working quickly.
>> Go, go.
>> PROBST: The orange team is
heading out.
They have their first bundle of
pieces.
Dreamz trying to figure it out.
Quickly, the green team is
falling behind.
>> You want to try, Alex?
>> Give it to me.
>> PROBST: Alex now trying to
give it a shot for the green
team.
The orange team at their second
station now.
Green team still working on
their first bundle.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Yau-Man has the
second bundle.
They're heading to their next
station.
Alex has the first bundle for
the green team.
>> Dig, dig.
>> PROBST: Green team trying to
make up some time.
Orange team with a decent lead
as they head to their third
station.
Orange team now at their final
Yau-Man working quickly on the
third bundle for the orange
team.
He's got it and they're heading
to the finish.
Alex has the second bundle.
They're heading to their last
station.
>> Dig, dig, dig, you guys!
Dig hard!
Dig, dig!
Cassandra, Cassandra, dig!
>> Row, row, row!
>> PROBST: Green trying to
catch up.
Earl, Cassandra, Boo, Edgardo,
Yau-Man still with a big lead
as they head to the finish.
Green team now at the third and
final station.
They're working on that third
bag.
Alex has the last bundle.
Green team is heading to the
finish.
>> Row, man, keep rowing.
We're not moving.
>> PROBST: The orange team,
they're slowing down.
>> Come on, Dreamz.
Bring it home, baby!
>> PROBST: Dreamz, Alex,
Michelle, Stacy, Mookie, trying
to finish strong.
You're still in it!
>> Come on, guys, row!
>> We got it! Go!
>> Come on!
Row!
>> PROBST: Orange team has
clicked in.
Two people working on the
puzzle.
>> Come on, guys!
Come on!
>> That one.
>> He's got it!
>> Row, row, row!
>> How does this go in?
>> PROBST: Earl and Yau-Man
losing valuable time now.
>> Somebody do it.
I got all the pieces.
>> PROBST: Two people working
on the puzzle.
It's Michelle and Alex for the
green team.
>> That one.
Earl-- he's got it, Earl.
>> Forks in the middle, forks
in the middle and all the way
around.
By Yau, by Yau.
By your side!
>> Top right goes the arrows.
>> No, we know, we know.
>> PROBST: You have to get all
six pieces together.
Then you put them in their spot
on the mask.
>> Come on, guys!
>> Okay.
>> Right behind, there.
Right in front of you.
>> Got this one, too.
>> Spear, fork, sail.
>> Start putting them in, guys.
>> Sail-- you got the sail?
>> Yeah, that's it, that's it,
that's it!
Put it in!
No, no, no, you had it!
No, Yau, you just had it.
There you go.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man makes a
last-minute switch, and it's a
good thing he did.
(cheering)
Orange team wins immunity and
reward!
>> Good teamwork!
Good teamwork.
Good teamwork. Good teamwork.
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
(applause)
No Tribal Council tonight.
In addition, you will feast--
steak, wine, some veggies.
Michelle, Stacy, Alex, Mookie,
Dreamz, all I have for you is a
date with me at Tribal Council
and this note.
I'll now read the note.
"You will not be going back to
camp.
There will be no time to
strategize.
We're heading to Tribal Council
right now."
Head down.
Let's go.
(Orange team cheers)
>> Whoo!
>> See you tonight.
Take care.
>> Dinner, yeah!
>> MVP or VIP, both.
>> We're going to pop open this
bottle of wine immediately.
>> Yeah.
>> Is it?
Where's the salt?
>> Whoo!
(laughter)
>> It went down like-- it went
down like this... whoa!
>> I can feel it going down.
>> We're going to be running...
we're going to be streaking
naked.
>> I don't want to cook because
we have so little, if I mess it
up, then I'll get beat up.
>> That's what Boo does for a
living, he cooks.
>> That challenge saved my butt.
If we hadn't been divided into
teams, I would have been gone.
There's no question.
You know, I dodged a bullet.
That's good.
>> That meat looks glorious.
>> And besides that, we all got
steaks and sautéed vegetables.
It was nice.
It brought my spirits back up.
>> Man, victory is sweet.
>> I didn't want to go to
Tribal Council, man.
>> I know.
>> Can't strategize, can't
conspire...
Straight from the challenge.
>> Hey, wink at somebody.
>> That's going to be hard.
>> That's crazy.
>> It might be something really
crazy that happens, that
somebody we didn't even think
they would vote off would be
gone.
>> I'm a little bit worried
about Alex right now.
I hope he doesn't get voted out
because if he gets voted out,
all my plans will be like, all
the strategies that I worked for
the last 24 days will be gone.
But, uh, Mookie has the idol
right now, and maybe, you know,
he can use the idol smartly.
You know what pisses me off?
The chance that we didn't get to
say bye to the person.
>> Yeah, man.
>> That sucks that we can't do
that.
>> Who do you think they're
going to vote out?
>> I think it's a toss-up
between Stacy and Michelle.
>> I think it will be Stacy.
>> It can be a surprise, though.
If Michelle is gone, I'm
definitely concerned about the
future, 'cause she's a key
component in my strategy.
So I'm really keeping my fingers
crossed that, uh, she's still
alive.
This is going to be a very, very
interesting vote, 'cause you're
going to get a lot of truth
from people.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Rocky and Lisi voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Dreamz, tell me about the merge.
Was it exciting?
Was it bad news?
What was your reaction?
>> I felt it was like day one
all over again except this
time people already know people.
So it was all the same to me
'cause I had friends from the
old Moto and friends from the
new Ravu, so I was pretty, I was
pretty happy with that.
>> PROBST: Alex, what was your
reaction when you got to the
beach and found out you were
really going back to the
original Moto?
>> Kind of a "holy crap."
I was shocked.
I mean, when I got there, I
was, like, "This is not good.
This is not going to be fun."
>> PROBST: Mookie, can you
start to feel paranoia setting
in already?
>> Definitely feel the paranoia.
I mean, people are developing
different relationships, and
you kind of lose yourself in
it, and you don't know where
you stand anymore.
And definitely you feel the
paranoia, especially on the
hot seat again.
>> PROBST: Why are you on the
hot seat?
>> I think everybody here is on
the hot seat.
We weren't able to talk to each
other.
And so now we're here not being
able to devise a plan, not being
able to talk to each other,
understand where our stances are
on who we think should go,
and that makes me paranoid.
>> PROBST: Stacy, so here you
sit now, getting ready to vote
somebody out with no idea what
everybody else is thinking.
How uncomfortable are you?
>> Um, it's pretty
uncomfortable.
I think it's a toss-up.
Right now my head is spinning
a little bit because there's a
group here and there's a group
there and there's a group to the
right and the left and behind
you, and everybody is thinking
about different scenarios and
different alliances.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, give me a
reason to get rid of Stacy.
>> One good reason for me to
vote out Stacy is because it
ain't me.
>> PROBST: Michelle, give me a
good reason to get rid of
Dreamz.
>> Me and Dreamz haven't really
talked much about strategy, so
I can't really say who he's in
an alliance with.
It's a fear of the unknown.
>> PROBST: Mookie, what's a good
reason you should get rid
of Michelle?
>> I mean guess one thing about
Michelle is, uh, we had a
relationship at the old Ravu,
and we were good then, but she
could have switched to a
different side.
That's something I'll have to
think about in the next, I don't
know how many minutes, you know,
and determine who could be the
biggest threat, and who can, you
know, strengthen my alliance.
>> PROBST: Michelle, give me a
good reason to get rid of Alex.
>> I think the biggest reason
to get rid of Alex is that he's
a threat in challenges.
He performs very well every
time.
And when it comes down to
immunity being so important
now, it's definitely a threat.
>> PROBST: Alex, give me a
reason to get rid of Stacy.
>> I don't really have a good
reason to get rid of Stacy,
Jeff.
>> PROBST: Give me a reason to
get rid of Michelle.
>> I don't know Michelle as well
as I know anyone else on this
tribe right now.
>> PROBST: Give me a reason to
get rid of Mookie.
>> I don't have a reason to get
rid of Mookie.
>> PROBST: Give me a reason to
get rid of Dreamz.
>> I don't have a reason to get
rid of Dreamz.
>> PROBST: Dreamz, do you think
as people speak here tonight,
that they are speaking not only
to me to answer a question, but
also to everybody else here to
kind of say "here's what I'm
thinking" by giving me their
answer?
>> He just let you know whose
name he's putting on the paper.
He don't have to talk to me.
He's one of the people I do
trust in the game.
So I understand where he's
coming from.
>> PROBST: Mookie, how do you
think this will change the game,
tonight's vote?
>> I think it's going to reveal
some things to the other guys
that are eating steak right now.
And they're going to see who's
been telling the truth and who
has been lying.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
If somebody does have the hidden
immunity idol, and it turns out
you want to play it tonight, you
would present it to me before I
read the votes.
It's time to vote.
Alex, you're up.
>> Sorry, Michelle.
It's nothing personal.
I'm just playing the game.
>> You were on the list
of people to go.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want
to play it, now is the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Stacy.
Michelle.
One vote Stacy, one vote
Stacy.
Two votes Stacy,
one vote Michelle.
Michelle.
We're tied.
Two votes Michelle,
two votes Stacy.
One vote left.
Ninth person voted out and the
third member of our jury:
Michelle.
You need to bring me your torch.
Michelle, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, it was clear tonight's
vote will have a major impact
on this game.
And there are five people
waiting back at camp eager to
know exactly what that impact
will be.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Mookie confronts Dreamz about
his vote at Tribal Council...
...and the fireworks begin.
>> I am irritated with
Cassandra.
She just made the worst mistake
of her life.
>> I'm not going to deceive
y'all.
>> PROBST: And Dreamz can't
keep quiet.
>> Survivor has been an amazing
experience.
I think my alliance is a little
weaker now that I'm not there.
Earl is going to have to find
himself a new spy.
But I think I've just affirmed
I know what kind of person I
am, and I know what I'm capable
of, and that I'm just as strong
as I thought.