>> JEFF PROBST: We are flying
over the stunning water of the
Fiji Islands, a place once known
for its cannibalism, uncharted
reefs, and formidable warriors.
These islands are home to
spectacular sea life and lush,
jagged terrain.
Just below are 19 strangers
that represent an extreme
cross-section of America, from a
former homeless street performer
to a Harvard-educated lawyer.
They have been given absolutely
no information.
The fear of the unknown is so
strong that one survivor quit
just moments before being set
adrift miles from shore.
Exile Island is back, with
hundreds of deadly sea snakes.
And this time, two hidden
immunity idols will complicate
the game like never before.
39 days, 19 people, one
survivor.
>> When I got there, I noticed
we were, like, all 19 of us
together.
I thought that Jeff was going to
be there and we were going to
be, like, split into tribes, and
"You go this way and you go the
other way."
But it wasn't the case.
>> In my past, where I used to
work and stuff, they called me
Stallone.
They called me... I guess I look
like Sylvester Stallone or
Rocky.
I have droopy eyes, dark hair.
For some reason James was too
hard for them to remember, so
Rocky will suffice.
>> We were just so excited to
get here, it didn't matter what
we were doing.
We were lost on a deserted
island, you know?
What would anybody do?
Go explore.
>> Oh, it's water!
>> Yeah, water!
>> Water!
>> Where?
>> Filled my canteen.
I'll tell you right now, I lost
my mind.
I didn't know what to do, I
didn't know what to say.
I was running around like a
chicken with my head cut off.
>> We look, and there's this
big, beautiful cave.
We're like, "This is a blessing.
We're like, "We're great."
>> I found a lemon tree.
>> We've got banana trees over
there.
We've got papaya over there.
We are stoked.
>> Well, my real name is Andre.
But on this beach I go by
Dreamz.
I came up with the name Dreamz a
long time ago.
It was more of a name of
striving and achievement.
>> I'm glad we came up here.
Now, look at this.
It's like buying a new house.
You know, you want to see
everything-- the backyard, the
front yard, living room, the
dining room.
You want to see everything
that's in your house.
And this is our house.
I'm the king of Fiji, of an
unnamed island.
>> My outdoor experience up to
this point consisted of being
maybe 20 to 40 feet off the
road.
This is totally new for me--
sleeping outdoors, finding food.
I love coconut, but it's
granulated, already shredded in
the grocery store.
So...
>> It is, I see.
>> But believe me, it's worth
it.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Okay?
>> Wow!
So you're a native, huh?
>> I'm native, almost.
I am definitely trying to prove
myself.
I can see that all the other
guys are quite young, like half
my age.
Old people are usually the first
ones to get booted off, so I'm
hoping I will be the exception
here because I know the
surroundings, and I can help get
them coconut to drink.
>> Did you just open that?
Oh, thanks!
>> So what are you thinking
right now?
>> Man, I don't know.
Too many people in one place
right now.
That's what makes me a little
bit nervous.
>> Yeah.
>> What do you think?
>> I mean, there's 19 of us.
So how do you split that up into
two tribes?
>> We're like, you know, looking
around the island for a machete.
We're looking for, like, flags
for our tribe.
We don't have a pot, we don't
have water, we don't have
anything.
We don't even know our tribe
name, you know?
It's incredibly overwhelming,
because there are so many people
and none of us have a clue
what's going on.
We're looking for Jeff Probst.
We're like, "Where's Jeff?"
>> Come on, we've got visitors!
>> Bring it in!
>> Where's the box?
>> I think they got it.
>> Oh, they got it?
>> Yeah.
>> We have a box!
>> Our heroes!
>> It's got a genie in it!
>> Everybody was excited.
Maybe we can get a machete.
Maybe we can get fire.
Everybody was anticipating what
they wanted to be in that box.
>> Wait, that can't be the way
into the box.
>> Rocky!
Rocky!
>> Whoa!
>> The strongest guys start,
like, throwing that thing down,
hammering it, punching it.
And here comes the little
scrawny guy, Yau-Man.
And he opens the whole thing
like, you know, in ten seconds.
>> It takes a real man to do it.
>> Very simple physics.
The weakest point is to drop it
on its corner.
So I dropped it on its corner
twice, and the box opened up.
>> Listen up.
This is very important.
>> "Welcome survivors.
Before you do anything else, you
must find the hidden cache of
lumber and supplies.
Its location is shown on the
map."
>> Tree mail, right here.
>> "Use the supplies to
construct the best possible
living area you can using the
blueprints provided as your
guide."
>> We've got a toilet seat on
there.
>> What?
>> Toilet assembly.
>> "Included with this note is a
flint to start fire.
Make sure you boil your water
before drinking.
Do not waste any time."
>> Let's rock 'n' roll.
>> You know, we've got this map
and directions and instructions
that says, you know, we have to
build a shelter, kitchen, and a
toilet and a picnic table.
>> Initially, naively, I
thought, "Wow, this is awesome."
And then I thought, "Wait a
minute, this is Survivor.
This is going to mean something
very cruel is going to happen
very soon."
>> Let's go do it.
>> Excuse me, brother.
>> Okay.
Here's the fork.
Go straight this way.
>> It's got to be right there.
>> Yeah.
>> I think I found it.
>> Holy cow!
>> All right, all right!
>> Ah!
>> What we found at the top of
the hill was just all kinds of
lumber.
And it was, like, shingles for
the roof of the shelter.
There was all these crazy things
that no one in their right minds
would ever imagine that we
were going to get when we got
here.
>> Look at all the tools!
>> Nails, hammers!
>> We got a bag of rice the
first day we were here. brother.
You know, maybe a machete and
bucket to boil water-- that's
what anybody was expecting.
No way... we have a toilet seat.
I'll say it again, a toilet
seat.
>> Okay, you, you, and you carry
all that stuff down.
>> One on each shoulder.
>> Give me that toilet seat.
I've never seen where people
that come on Survivor have this
much, so I'm really nervous,
because I think a curve ball is
coming.
It's too easy.
>> The kitchen's going to be
right there, okay?
The outhouse will be over there.
There was a site plan, and being
an architect, of course, I was
given all of the maps and said,
"Here, you figure out what to
do."
So I looked at the site plan and
realized the cave was, in fact,
the location of the shelter.
Then there would be a kitchen
and an outhouse, and it was...
it's a pretty amazing set of
drawings.
So we're building.
Who's got the site plan?
>> There's our shovels, all
right?
>> We need the shovel brigade to
start shoveling four holes.
That's our number one thing.
Who's got the shovel?
Who's got the site plan?
Who's got the tape measure?
We need a crew for the kitchen,
or else it won't be done until
tomorrow.
>> I do get the sense that
Sylvia's trying to dominate.
You know, we're all here to do
this together, and you're going
to upset the wagon by doing
that.
>> He's what?
All right, here's what's going
to happen-- whenever there is a
big word in a sentence, we're
all going to have a time-out and
teach James the big word, the
definition.
>> There's another big word
James... orthagonal, huh?
Learn something new every day,
right?
( cheers )
>> All right!
>> Proud of you!
>> When we started construction,
everybody was, like, trying to,
like, you know, prove to other
people that they can handle the
workload.
But as, you know, the workload
started going on and on, and the
people started going out in
couples, you could see that some
people were talking.
>> I'm trying to talk to people
and see what's going on so I
can... you know, so I can get my
place here.
>> Okay.
>> So right now, just me, you.
>> We need a guy.
>> We do need a guy.
>> Who?
>> I don't know.
Me and Jessica have kind of
got... you know, we're talking,
getting some stuff... getting
some stuff together.
We don't really know what's
going to happen, so I think I
need to be talking to as many
people as I can.
>> No, y'all are just being
silly.
This water its too hot to drink.
>> Just drink it, man.
>> It just burned me.
I ain't going to drink it.
It burned me.
>> So you guys want to... when
you're done with the water, do
you want to help with the
bathroom, or do you want to
start with the kitchen?
I feel like it's not moving
nearly as fast as it should,
because we're still working on
the primary shelter when the
kitchens and bathroom still need
to be built.
We've got to get everything done
okay?
So put down...
>> We need to get this done,
because we're running out of
light.
And we have to have this done.
>> The night was rough.
There we are with the shelter
half done, no roof, half a
floor, and we ended up getting
soaked.
So today we need to finish our
shelter.
>> Can you, you know, lead a
bunch of people to bring all the
material down?
>> It should be a two-by-four.
>> Two-by-four?
Well....
>> This is a cup.
Hold on to it.
This is the funnel.
>> Yau-Man, he's a keeper.
He figures out every little
thing that goes on.
>> Drink in good health.
>> Good hot tea.
>> Lemon.
>> We're getting together.
All 19 of us are bonding.
I don't know if it's a good
thing or a bad thing, but it's
bonding us.
Oh, my god!
That looks beautiful!
>> We're rockin'.
I'm taking this one home.
We've been here almost two days
trying to figure out what's
going on.
I think we just keep getting to
know each other until we get to
the point where we get the next
set of instructions.
>> We have a shelter.
It has a floor and a roof.
We're going to have a kitchen.
We have an outhouse with an
actual toilet.
It's really surprising to have
so much on day two.
>> We're feeling pretty lucky
right now.
I mean, this is my Fiji vacation
I mean, we have everything that
we need.
I'm scared about what's coming.
>> All of your hard work to make
this place kind of a home for
now!
>> Nice!
>> ( applause )
>> Everybody!
Everybody!
>> I can't take all the credit.
Okay, I can.
But I just want to thank all my
people for getting me coconuts
while I was working.
Back as a child, I was pretty
much homeless.
By the age of seven, I was out
of a house and just stayed in
the back of a soup kitchen.
And then go into the trash cans
and get the food.
And it... I mean, it was kind of
like what's going on right now.
The only thing you have to worry
about is when it rains or when
you can't find no more food.
I love it.
I wish I could bring my family
from home here.
>> What kind of name is Earl?
>> Dreamz?
>> What kind of name is Dreamz?
>> Who said that?
Who said that?
Back there.
Is that a Chinese person that
said that?
My thing is to be playful and
play too much, just to make sure
they notice that I'm present, to
know that my presence is there.
Were you as great as I, you
could say what you want to say.
>> You know what?
>> Is he going to be quiet at
all tonight?
>> Dreamz kind of came out of
nowhere, like, late, while we
were all trying to sleep.
He was going off on little
rants, like, every 15 to 20
minutes.
>> Where all the white people
here?
If you're white, raise your
hand.
Rock, what color are you, man?
>> I'm Italian, Irish, and
Spanish.
>> You're talking to him or are
you going to talk to me?
>> Just yelling about nonsense.
And I'm exhausted.
I don't know if the island is
getting to him, but he's just
getting a little irritating.
Why don't you give me two
seconds to talk, and then you
can speak and we'll be done.
>> Go ahead, talk.
>> All right, you get a little
crazy sometimes.
>> Just talk.
>> I'm talking right now.
I'm talking to you right now.
You get a little jumpy with your
voice.
You snap, you snap... I don't
care what you do with anybody
else, you snap a little bit at
me.
All right, I'm telling you right
now, I don't want to be treated
like that.
Okay?
I'm just trying to go to sleep.
I've been running around all
day.
I don't need you to raise your
voice to me.
Because I'm not a little girl.
>> I don't yell at people.
That's not me.
>> What are you doing now?
>> I'm talking to you.
I'm talking to you.
I haven't yelled at anybody
here.
>> You're crazy, dude.
>> And I'm not going to let
anybody belittle me.
>> What do I stand to gain by
belittling you?
What do I stand to gain?
>> I don't know.
Why?
>> Because you yelled at me!
That's why, that's why!
>> You are yelling right now.
>> Because you don't pay
attention.
I'm trying to explain it to you.
>> No, you yelled.
>> Go back to bed.
Go back to bed and hang out with
your friends.
>> Whatever, Rock.
>> I'm pretty hard on myself
when it comes to, like, letting
my emotions show.
I hate to do it.
I used to do it when I was
young, and I think I'm past that
now.
But it's just really hard,
especially under the conditions
we're under right now.
What am I supposed to do?
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Welcome to Survivor: Fiji.
Jessica, tell me about the first
few moments.
You hit the beach.
What happens?
>> It was wild.
It was like a big beach party.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, I dropped a
package out of the sky.
Tell me about the reaction.
>> Someone found the canister
and decided to open it and saw
the plans.
And it's not just any shelter.
It looks like a very fancy
shelter.
And we're supposed to build it.
>> PROBST: Alex, when you
started to assemble the shelter,
did anybody emerge as the
driving force on how to approach
this?
>> I think initially we were all
pretty confused, but luckily, we
have an architect on board.
So...
>> Who's the architect?
>> Sylvia.
>> Sylvia right here.
>> So, I mean, having an
architect on here was extremely
helpful.
>> PROBST: So the first big task
is to build the shelter.
And Sylvia, this is what you do
every day.
>> I was so happy.
I couldn't believe it.
>> PROBST: So it sounds like,
Sylvia, you really stepped up to
be the leader.
Does that ring true to everybody
here?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Nobody disagrees with
that?
>> Nope.
>> PROBST: Sylvia, come on over.
You are now going to divide
these 18 people into two tribes.
You're going to alternate, one
person to the green line, one
person to the orange line.
Make your first choice, Sylvia.
>> Cassandra to the green line.
>> PROBST: Cassandra, first
member of the unnamed green
tribe.
Next choice, somebody going to
the orange line.
>> Yeah, Michelle.
>> PROBST: Michelle.
Next choice?
>> Liliana.
>> PROBST: Liliana joins
Cassandra.
Has the green top to match the
green tribe.
Next choice.
>> Erica.
>> PROBST: Erica joins Michelle.
Make your next choice.
>> Stacy, on the green.
>> PROBST: Stacy joins the green
tribe.
Make your next choice.
>> Rita.
>> PROBST: Rita joins Michelle
and Erica.
Lisi.
>> Lisi, thank you.
>> PROBST: Lisi joins Cassandra,
Liliana and Stacy.
>> PROBST: Next choice.
>> Jessica.
>> PROBST: Jessica joins
Michelle, Erica, and Rita.
Okay.
>> Dreamz to green.
>> PROBST: Dreamz joins the
green tribe.
Make your next choice.
>> Boston to orange.
>> PROBST: Boston.
Is that what you're going by,
Boston?
>> I've got a bunch of
nicknames, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Give me one so I know
what to call you.
>> Rocky, Rocky.
>> PROBST: Rocky joins Michelle,
Erica, Rita, and Jessica.
>> Boo to the green.
>> PROBST: Boo joins the green
tribe.
>> Earl, orange.
>> PROBST: Earl joins Michelle,
Erica, Rita, Jessica, and Rocky.
>> Big Gary to the green.
>> PROBST: Gary goes to green.
>> All right!
>> PROBST: we have a nickname
for Gary, too?
>> Wild Man to orange.
That's my nickname for him.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man joins
Michelle, Erica, Rita, Jessica,
Rocky, and Earl.
Continue on.
>> The sexy guy in the green
tank top.
>> PROBST: Alex joins the green
tribe.
Make your next choice.
>> Anthony.
>> PROBST: Anthony joins the
orange tribe.
Sylvia.
>> Big Ed to the green.
>> PROBST: Edgardo goes to the
green tribe.
Mookie goes to the orange tribe.
We have our two tribes.
Moto.
You are green.
Ravu, you are orange.
Put on your buffs.
>> Whoo-hoo-hoo!
>> PROBST: Okay, Sylvia, here's
what's going to happen.
You are not on a tribe.
You are still in the game.
You're going to Exile Island.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Bad news, you will
have company.
Thousands of sea snakes out
there.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: The good news is
you'll receive a clue to the
whereabouts of a hidden immunity
idol.
Secondly, because are you not on
a tribe, you are immune from the
first tribal council.
You will rejoin this game by
joining the tribe that does lose
a member.
Boat's waiting for you.
Exile Island awaits.
>> Bye, Sylvia!
Good luck.
>> Take care of yourself, woman.
>> Be safe.
Be safe.
>> PROBST: All right, let's go
to today's challenge.
For today's challenge, you are
going to race chariots across
the Fijian mud flats.
Two people will be on the
chariot.
The other seven will pull you
across a quarter-mile course.
Along the way, the two people on
the chariot are responsible for
retrieving three bags of puzzle
pieces.
When you reach the end of the
course, you'll grab a tribe
flag, come all the way back.
Four tribe members will then use
those puzzle pieces to solve
three puzzles.
This will give you the numbers
you need to solve a combination
wheel.
You will turn it clockwise,
counter-clockwise, clockwise.
If you count correctly, you will
find a knife.
You'll take the knife, chop a
rope, dropping a tribe flag.
First tribe to drop their flag
wins the challenge.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The most important
thing in this game, immunity.
( applause )
Winning tribe gets immunity, is
safe from the first tribal
council.
In addition to immunity, the
winning tribe gets to stay on
the beach that all 19 of you put
blood, sweat, and tears into
building.
>> All right, we can do this.
We can do this.
>> PROBST: And when you get
back, there will be a
housewarming gift waiting for
you-- goblets, cutlery, a couple
of hammocks, a bush shower, and
a nice, soft, comfortable couch.
>> I think we got it.
>> PROBST: Losers will go to a
new beach where you will find
one pot and one machete, and
that's it.
In addition, losers are going to
tribal council tonight.
Somebody will be the first
person voted out.
Give you a minute to strategize
and we'll get started.
On the chariot for Ravu,
Michelle, Jessica.
On the chariot for Moto, Lisi,
Stacy.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Pull, pull!
>> Little further, little
further, little further.
>> PROBST: Stacy working on the
knots, Jessica working on the
knots for Ravu.
Stacy whipping through those
knots.
>> Go, Stacy!
>> PROBST: Jessica slowing down
a little for Ravu.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Jessica still working
on the pieces.
>> Okay, I'm almost done.
>> Come on, Jessica!
>> PROBST: Moto at the second
bag.
Ravu has their first bag.
They're off.
Stacy working on those pieces.
>> Keep going, keep going, keep
going.
Michelle now working for Ravu,
trying to make up some time.
>> Go, baby girl.
Come on.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: Moto has their second
bag of pieces.
They're heading out.
Moto reaches their third bag.
Ravu has their second bag.
They're still in it.
>> Go, go, go, go!
Come on, push!
Push!
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> Slow down!
>> PROBST: Stacy working on that
third and final bag.
She has it.
Moto heading for their flag.
Michelle trying to pick up some
ground for Ravu.
She's doing it.
They're making up time.
>> Push!
Push!
>> PROBST: Moto has their flag
and they're heading back.
Ravu has their flag.
They're heading back.
>> Come on!
Push, push, push!
>> Hustle!
Hustle!
>> They're catching up.
Come on, guys.
>> Let's go, guys!
We're there!
We're so there!
>> Stop!
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Moto stumbles.
Ravu now in the lead.
>> Push!
Harder!
>> Go, go!
>> Come on, guys!
We can't lose!
We've got this!
You guys, we're almost there.
You're doing so good.
>> PROBST: Earl leading his
tribe.
Dreamz slowing down.
>> We've still got the puzzle.
Let's keep forcing.
>> PROBST: Moto losing some
ground.
>> Come on, push!
>> Come on, you guys, you're
doing great!
>> PROBST: Ravu first back to
the puzzle table.
Four people solving the puzzle.
Moto has got to touch.
Release.
Four people, start solving the
puzzles.
You have three puzzles.
Each puzzle will give you a
number.
You will need that number to
find the knife.
>> Take your time.
Don't panic, don't panic.
>> PROBST: Ravu has their first
puzzle solved.
>> You guys are geniuses.
Come on.
>> PROBST: Immunity and a huge
reward on the line.
Moto working on their second
puzzle, making up a lot of
ground.
>> Let's go, folks.
>> PROBST: Moto has two puzzles
completed.
Ravu, you need to pick it up.
>> Come on, come on, come on.
Pick it up, pick it up, pick it
up!
>> PROBST: Moto working on their
third puzzle.
Ravu still struggling with their
second.
>> You guys got it.
You guys got it.
>> PROBST: Ravu has their second
puzzle.
They're now working on their
third puzzle.
>> I need the rest of an S.
>> All right, do it!
>> PROBST: Moto has all three
puzzles completed.
They need to solve the
combination and find the knife.
Ravu, you are still in it.
>> You are so still in it.
Come on!
>> PROBST: Jessica struggling to
figure it out.
>> One, two, three, four...
>> PROBST: Moto very close.
Moto thinks they have it.
Moto wins immunity and reward!
All right, Moto,
congratulations.
Immunity.
Nobody going home tonight.
Equally exciting, you are going
back to a beach that's all
waiting for you, already
constructed.
You've got fire and you've got
some really nice housewarming
gifts.
Ravu, here's a map to your new
beach.
Not much waiting for you-- a pot
and a machete.
Tonight, tribal council with me.
One of the nine of you is going
home.
Head to your new camp.
I'll see you tonight.
>> Whoo!
>> We're going to enjoy this
reward, baby!
>> Oh, my god, I'm so excited.
>> We've got a couch!
>> Having that first win is such
a huge thing for morale.
We come back to our shelter, and
we've got this great couch.
And I almost shed a tear, I was
so happy.
>> Oh, thank you, lord!
>> All right!
Candles.
>> We got hammocks.
>> Shower!
>> We've got a beer mug.
>> Dreamz.
>> Oh, cool.
>> Give me that one, baby.
>> It feels so spectacular.
Not only did we get immunity,
not only did we go back to the
place we helped put together.
We came back with a kick-ass
tribe.
All right, to us, guys!
>> To Moto!
>> Ironically enough, Sylvia,
she helped build this place, and
now she's sleeping with the
snakes.
>> When I found out I was being
exiled to Exile Island, Jeff was
very clear that it was good and
there was bad.
The bad was that I would be here
by myself with a bunch of sea
snakes.
Jeff had wander me about these
sea snakes and I thought he was
trying to pull my chain, you
know.
But it's for real.
I see them still.
I see them.
Oh, boy.
The good was that I got the
immunity.
And there would be a clue giving
me some kind of hint about where
the immunity idol was hidden.
Wow, pretty spectacular.
>> "Here you won't find the idol
you crave.
Search back at your camp if you
hope to be saved."
Okay.
I've been given this opportunity
of a clue.
But the clue said, "Sorry, it's
not here.
It's back at camp."
So now I have to figure out a
time and a place where I can
search for it without prying
eyes.
That's going to be a challenge
in itself.
>> We're home.
>> Losing the challenge today
felt horrible.
All the work we put into the
shelter, you know, learning the
island, just everything, you
know, you get accustomed to,
it's gone.
>> We have a cave right there.
>> Awesome.
This is awesome!
This place is so nice!
>> Is it amazing?
>> I'm glad we lost.
( laughter )
Keep their stupid shower.
>> Yeah, that cave is gorgeous.
The hardest part for me was not
being able to go back to that
shelter that we built.
But, I mean, everybody else
seems like they're okay.
It's like, "Whatever.
Oh, we lost it, but we're over
here on this great island."
I mean, they're enjoying the
blankets and pillows and the
couch.
We have to start all over.
I'm pissed off, and I can't
believe nobody else is.
We worked hard on building that
shelter, kitchen.
We worked hard.
And that hurt the most.
>> Right now, we're back at
square one, because we have
nothing.
And at the same time, we've got
to figure out a team member to
lose.
>> Yeah.
>> Don't get sad.
>> Oh, I'm not sad.
>> All right, I'm just telling
you.
We've got to figure out.
Me... maybe me, you, and Jess,
we'll figure it out, yeah?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> All right.
>> Me, Jessica, and Rocky are
really tight.
We can swing the whole thing.
>> And Michelle... Michelle,
she's a little ninja guy.
She hangs from things, she jumps
around, she's really physically
fit, and that's what we need
right now.
>> I'm not getting rid of
Monkey.
I call her Monkey.
>> Like I said, I...
>> We need strong people.
Rita has to go because Erica is
strong.
>> Erica is no joke.
>> Yeah, she's, like... she's
the real deal.
So...
>> Okay?
>> Yeah.
>> All right?
All right, and what a tangled
web we weave.
It just sucks, Jess, because I
don't want to get rid of
anybody.
>> I know.
I feel bad, too.
>> I don't want to get rid of
anybody, but it's the game,
right?
What are you going to do?
>> We just have to stick
together.
>> We will.
I just feel so safe with Rocky.
I feel good now that I know it's
not me, because I was working on
that puzzle.
We lost on the puzzle.
>> We're thinking Jessica.
>> Who?
>> Jessica.
>> She's dispensable.
Her third puzzle was hers.
>> I mean, I hear you that
point.
But could the third one have
been harder?
Was it harder?
>> They were all same.
>> They were all kind of the
same?
>> Yeah.
>> That's a valid point.
>> It's over here, right?
>> I will.
>> That way I know, all right?
>> I will, because me, you and
Erica are going to stick
together.
>> Yeah.
>> I will tell you.
>> We were all kind of pointing
at Jessica.
We all adore her.
It's nothing personality-wise.
I get along super good with her.
So I'm kind of hurting to have
to do that.
>> My concern is to really keep
all the strong guys.
>> I would say Rita's stronger
than Jessica.
She is.
>> I have, too.
>> Just don't think on a
personal level.
Just think the next challenge.
>> Dude, this is business.
>> They just came to a
conclusion that Jessica has to
be voted out.
I... I won't write Jessica's
name down.
I'm not going to do it.
>> Who?
How do you know that?
And how did that come about?
>> I don't know how it came
about.
I just know it.
>> Just tell me who you heard it
from.
Huh?
Everybody?
Well, I'm not putting her name
down.
I won't put her name down.
>> Me neither.
>> Tribal council tonight will
be interesting.
Everybody's nervous, and you
still wonder in the back of your
mind-- like, it might be you.
Always keep your guard up.
You never know when people are
trying to trick you.
It's a lot of actors here, a lot
of poker faces.
This is my poker face.
>> PROBST: Go ahead and grab a
torch.
Approach the flame.
Dip it in, get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
tribal council.
As long as you have fire, you're
still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
Take a seat.
Michelle, how frustrating is it
right now to know that there are
nine people sleeping peacefully
in a shelter you helped build?
>> It was a frustrating thought
at first, but I think it's okay
now.
We actually really like our new
island.
>> PROBST: I can't wait to hear
how you've turned this in your
head.
Erica, what's so great about
the new island that you don't
miss the old one?
>> We have an abundance of
coconut.
>> PROBST: 36 days left.
You better have a lot of
coconuts.
>> I mean, it's not a fantasy
land.
The reality is, we don't have
fire.
And without the fire, we don't
have water.
You know, and I'm glad everybody
has themselves together, and
we're going to make it work.
But it's going to take hard
work.
And it starts immediately.
>> PROBST: James, how big of an
advantage is it for the other
tribe to not only have shelter,
but to have fire, to have water?
>> I think they have a huge
advantage right now, but I think
this group's got something
special.
I think we're going to rise
above and hopefully knock them
off their perch the next time we
go against them in the
challenge.
>> PROBST: So now you've got to
vote somebody out.
You haven't had much time really
to even assess why you would
keep somebody or why you would
get rid of somebody.
So Erica, what do you use for
the criteria?
>> I think we're going to fall
behind if we lose another
challenge.
We know everybody has something
good to offer, but somebody has
to go.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, you've got
to be a little concerned, with
all due respect, simply due to
age.
>> Yes, I feel very vulnerable,
because I'm not... physically
not the strongest one.
And in order to win the next
challenge, I want to keep all
the strong guys.
And if everybody thinks like
that, I think I'm going to be a
target, and I hope they don't.
>> PROBST: Mookie, will this
tribe be better after tonight's
vote?
>> It's hard to say.
I think my vote's based upon
whether that person can be
replaced by Sylvia.
Does she or he contribute enough
or more than Sylvia would?
>> PROBST: Rocky, do you think
the person voted out tonight
will be surprised?
>> Yeah.
I think so.
Because I know if I'm voted off,
I'm surprised.
I'm sure if anybody here,
surprise, too.
So yeah, I bet there will be a
big surprise coming up real
soon.
>> PROBST: Rita, if it's you
tonight, do you understand why
they would get rid of you?
>> I would be very surprised.
Because I think that I am
contributing for us to get
ahead.
But I would understand.
>> PROBST: Mookie, if it's you,
would you understand?
>> No, I would not understand.
>> PROBST: Jessica, would you
understand?
>> No.
I mean, if I had been laying on
the beach, you know, getting
some sun and just relaxing, then
maybe, yes, but no.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Michelle, you're up.
>> I'm sorry.
This wasn't my idea.
>> Sorry.
Nothing personal here.
This is strictly mercenary.
I'm trying to stay alive to
fight another day.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the vote are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Mookie.
Rita.
Jessica.
Yau-Man.
That's one vote each for Jessica
Mookie, Rita, and Yau Man.
Jessica.
Two vote Jessica.
Three votes Jessica.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Fiji, Jessica.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Jessica, the tribe has spoken.
>> PROBST: Well, nearly half the
tribe got at least one vote.
Going to be a lot of people
wondering what they did to earn
a vote and what they can do
tomorrow to make sure it doesn't
happen again.
Because you do not have fire,
you will not be taking your
torches back with you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time
on Survivor:
>> Water.
Just lick some leafs, man.
>> Ravu gets weaker.
>> I'm starving, I'm thirsty.
>> Earl gets primal.
>> Sorry there, buddy-- I can't
take that chance.
>> Boo, be careful.
>> PROBST: And Boo's luck...
>> I need some medical.
I get injured a lot.
>> PROBST: ...runs out.
>> Boo will hurt himself out of
the game.
>> I guess if you're going to
get back-stabbed, it's good to
get it done in the beginning
when you don't know people that
well.
I was absolutely shocked.
I felt like I worked really
hard.
So I don't know where I went
wrong.
I feel honored to have been able
to play a game that not many
people get to play.
My torch may have been snuffed
here, but I'm sure it's being
lit somewhere else.