>> JEFF PROBST: I'm on the steps
of a 16th century Buddhist
monastery in one of the oldest
countries in the world, China.
16 Americans are beginning the
adventure of a lifetime in
ultramodern Shanghai.
But as their journey continues,
these 16 strangers are being
transported back in time.
Over the next 39 days, the
survivors will experience a
culture that dates back nearly
5,000 years.
These survivors come from a
wide variety of backgrounds.
A former Miss Montana.
A middle school lunch lady.
A Christian radio talk show
host.
A gay Mormon flight attendant.
A professional wrestler.
A University of South Carolina
honor student.
A chicken farmer from Virginia.
A professional poker player.
There's a fourth grade school
teacher, a Nashville musician.
A gravedigger from Louisiana.
A jewelry designer from Los
Angeles.
A New York City waitress.
A surfing instructor.
A bartender and former model.
And a 20-year-old student and
athlete, the youngest survivor
ever.
Their adventure will play out
in a remote section of China
where they will live in the
shadows of this temple on the
Lake of a Thousand Islands, a
harsh and remote land that will
challenge even the strongest of
survivors.
It is the ultimate challenge,
16 people, all from different
walks of life, forced to work
together to create a new
society while battling the
elements and each other.
They must learn to adapt or
they'll be voted out.
In the end, only one will
remain to claim the million
dollar prize.
39 days, 16 people, one
survivor.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> I walked in, and, you know,
it was an adventure for me.
I was just like a damn kid at a
carnival.
I ain't never been nowhere.
But I loved it.
>> Being Chinese, it's so
amazing coming to do Survivor
in China.
My grandfather passed away,
like, a couple of weeks ago.
And he would have just gotten
such a kick out of seeing me
here, you know.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Survivor:
China.
I hope you have enjoyed your
journey so far.
Before the game can begin,
you are going to participate
in a Buddhist ceremony inside
this 400-year-old temple.
I want to assure everybody,
because I realize everybody has
different beliefs, this is not
a worship ceremony.
The people of this land want
you to feel welcome.
That's the whole point.
So, when you're finished,
return back out here to me.
(chanting)
>> I work as a lunch lady
behind the counter in the
cafeteria, and to actually be
in a temple like that, what a
great experience.
It almost made me cry, to tell
you the truth.
It was just spiritual.
It was very emotional for me.
>> I'm a waitress from New York
City, dude.
What do you think?
Do you think I know how to do
any of this stuff?
I'm not trying to be a monk
here.
I'm tired.
I want to sit back with the
lemonade.
Like, I don't really want to be,
like, bowing 37 times.
And we bowed... we bowed for,
like, days.
I swear to God, we were there
forever.
>> I'm a believer in Jesus
Christ, and in the Bible it
says, "Thou shall not bow down
to any other god."
You know, it really felt like
worship.
I mean, we're in a temple.
There's the Buddha.
I just couldn't do it.
It was emotional for me.
Because I knew I did the right
thing.
But it was so hard.
>> PROBST: Okay, so, Leslie, you
didn't make it through the
whole ceremony.
What happened?
>> You know, I'm not a
religious person, but I have a
relationship with Jesus Christ,
and the only time I'm going to
put my face on the floor is for
him.
>> PROBST: So even though I had
said this was a welcome...
>> I really didn't want to be
disrespectful.
But it felt like worship.
>> PROBST: Worried that it might
impact the next 39 days?
>> You know, I'm really not.
I'm just going to play the game
and be me.
If they like me, great.
If they don't, you know, I'll
deal with that.
>> PROBST: A big theme in
Buddhism is the leaving behind
of your worldly possessions.
That applies to suitcases.
It means you will be going into
this game wearing the clothes
on your back.
>> Aarrggh!
>> These are, like, 20 pounds
each.
>> I don't have on a bra.
>> PROBST: Well, that's going to
make you either very popular...
(laughter)
...or a big liability if you let
it get in the way of challenges
or camp life.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, the game
is about to begin.
We're going to divide into
tribes.
There's a bag over here for
each of you with your name on
it.
Come find your bag, put on your
buff.
>> God!
>> Ashley.
>> PROBST: If you have yellow,
head to the left.
If you have red, head over here
to the right.
Put your buff.
Yellow tribe-- your name is
Zhan Hu, which means "fighting
tiger."
We have Frosti, Dave, Jaime,
Erik, Peih-gee, Sherea, Ashley,
and Chicken.
>> From the get go, I saw we
had a pretty strong team.
I'm the youngest and the
smallest guy out here, so I got
to prove my worth.
>> PROBST: Red tribe, your name
is Fei Long.
It means "flying dragon."
We have Jean-Robert, Leslie,
Amanda, Courtney, Denise,
James, Todd, and Aaron.
>> I am so happy to be a Fei
Long member.
Because I think James and Aaron
are definitely two of our
strongest members.
So, I think we're going to be a
powerhouse in challenges.
>> PROBST: All right, you are
about to engage in a battle.
For the next 39 days, you will
be involved in a struggle for
survival.
The single greatest document on
the history of strategy was
written by the Chinese,
The Art of War.
Look through this.
There is wisdom about strategy
in battle that could help you
win this game and the million
dollars.
(laughter)
I also have a map for each
tribe to your new home.
Fei Long, come get your Art of
War and your map.
Head out and go to the right.
The boat will be waiting for
you.
Zhan Hu, come get your Art of
War and your map.
Head out and go to the left of
the temple.
The boat will be waiting for
you.
Good luck, guys.
(applause)
>> The person farthest back has
the count.
>> I have a question, does
anybody know how to do this?
>> Let's just all calm down and,
like, nice and easy.
So we're all going straight
rather than spinning in circles.
So, we were on this lake in the
middle of China.
We have no idea where we are.
You know, it's like rice
paddies and tropical rain
forest.
And I don't think my tribe for
the most part knows what's
going on.
Right side, everybody.
Everybody, right side.
No left side.
I see myself as a leader, but I
try and do it as subtly as
possible.
I don't want the target on my
back.
(cheers)
>> Fei Long!
>> We've got a great team.
>> We do have a good team.
>> We've got, like, an axe
thing.
We've got rice, you guys!
>> Is that all that's in there,
is rice?
>> Yeah, just great big bag of
rice.
>> We're going to keep that
dry, you guys.
>> Oh, no.
It's raining.
>> What do you do, Todd?
>> I'm a flight attendant.
>> You're a flight attendant?
No way.
You are so cute.
>> I'm sorry, I am easily
irritated.
I seem like to be, like, sort
of marooned in a land of flight
attendants and Sunday school
teachers.
Like, come on.
I live in a city.
People who live in New York
don't act like this.
>> All right, let's do this.
Yeah, Fei Long!
>> This is like my own private
hell.
They're, like, exactly the kind
of people that I don't like
being around, who are all, like,
"Everything's always great.
Isn't it amazing?
Like you're doing a really good
job with that."
>> High five.
>> High five!
>> Yeah, dog.
Come on, now.
>> It's going to be our tree
mail, dude.
>> Oh, man.
>> There's nothing here.
>> You said you were a flight
attendant?
>> Yeah.
>> You really a flight
attendant?
>> Yeah, I really am.
>> For some reason, I don't... I
don't know.
>> You don't believe me?
>> It's like I kind of believe
you but...
>> Why would I lie about a job
like that?
>> I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know.
I like you.
I like you, but for some
reason, I... you seem a little
devious.
I'm a professional poker player.
And one of the strengths that I
have is my ability to read
players.
I'm just letting you know that
I know that you're sharp.
I don't know why.
My gut feeling tells me you're
particularly sharp.
My conversation with Todd was
deliberate.
I wanted him to know that,
"Listen, I know that you're the
clever guy.
Hey, I'm on to you.
Don't come this way, and we'll
be all right."
>> Right now, honestly, and I
mean this, is I really want to
be here.
Like, I just really, really,
really want to be here, and I
will do whatever to stay, you
know.
>> Jean-Robert was very right.
I will do whatever I need to do
to win that million dollars.
Can I ask you, though, to not
tell other people you think I'm
sharp?
>> I mean, I'm not saying that I
am, but I don't want to become
that one.
I can't have someone walking
around saying, "Watch out for
Todd."
I'm saying, "Watch out for
Jean-Robert" now.
I'm here to win a million
dollars.
It's a million dollars.
That's a lot of money.
>> We made it.
We got a pot.
I'm so hoping we'd have a pot.
What are we going to do about
shelter, something for the
night?
>> All right, let's start
thinking.
>> When I first walked up, I
have on a dress with heels.
I'm a southern girl, but I'm
not an outdoorsy girl, and this
situation is so disgusting and
so nasty.
Camp sucks.
This is way harder than I
expected.
>> Definitely build some kind
of lean-to with it.
>> Right.
>> I mean, if we can salvage any
of this...
>> Yeah.
>> It would be helpful.
>> Ready?
All right, good, good.
Watch that big piece of wood.
It's rotting.
It's... that's okay.
>> Let's think about this a
minute.
When you get that up, it
ain't going to be big enough for
all of us to sleep under, even
you can use that.
>> Okay, so what do you
suggest?
>> I suggest we build one.
>> Okay.
Well, let's build it.
>> This is essentially what we,
you know--
>> We could use the foundation
of the wood to build it.
>> Plus we have more back there.
>> I've got an opinion just
like everyone else.
Go ahead.
I'm from Virginia.
I lived in the woods.
I've got a lot of experience
over these characters.
Do you think this here is going
to hold up?
Seriously, come on.
>> We have to build something.
>> We have to build something,
though.
So let's stop being negative
and let's just start being
proactive.
>> I was just giving my
opinion, and nobody wanted it,
so I'm done suggesting, you
know.
I won't do that no more.
(loud noise)
>> Oh, God!
>> I'm sorry.
I've got a little gas.
I can't help it.
>> I don't mind, really.
I'm around wrestlers every day
of my life.
>> I seriously can't believe
you're a wrestler.
>> It's so fun.
It's the greatest job in the
world.
It's the funnest job ever.
I'm a WW Diva, and I wrestle
for a living.
I compete.
I think that it's probably
prepared me a great deal more
for this game.
I need to chop something up,
y'all.
Because there is that
competitive nature you have
within the locker room, and
that's a great positive that I'm
going to have going into this
game.
We are going to have a really
awesome shelter.
I don't want to go home a
loser, you know what I mean?
Because I know my fans are
going to want me to win.
Oh, hell, no, I can't dance at
all.
I'm the worst.
My girlfriends in the locker
room, like, they always play
music while we're getting ready.
I'm not doing it!
I can't.
>> I think I'm on the lazy
tribe.
Just seeing, like, half the
people wanting to just stand
around and talk about the most
ridiculous stuff I'd ever heard.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> What song?
>> It don't matter.
>> I can't connect to the
wackiness out here.
Like, I mean, I could probably
do it at home, but I just... I
feel like so serious.
>> Why can't we do the shelter
right here?
Because it's much more open and
cleaner than up there under the
trees.
>> Let's do it.
>> Honestly, we just need to
make a decision.
>> Why am I here?!
>> Oh, God, please help us.
(laughter)
>> I need some vines.
>> Is that helping, you guys?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's get more, though.
>> Yeah, oh, yeah.
>> Timber.
>> I just need a few more for
the bed.
>> You guys are, like, regular
lumbermen.
>> Timber!
>> We're getting a lot
accomplished with our shelter.
We are a very strong tribe.
We get along great, and we work
well together.
>> How you doing, James?
>> Hey, man.
>> I think James is amazing.
He's, like, Superman.
I've never seen... he just
works.
But I'm worried about James
because he's just been very
quiet.
I mean, you're an interesting
guy.
What do you do?
>> You bury people.
That's interesting.
Are you serious?
>> Yeah.
Yeah, I'm a grave digger.
I like that work because, you
know, I'm kind of by myself.
That's part of my problem over
here now.
I'm used to being by myself.
>> You know what, charm is
deceptive.
You be you and you'll be fine.
The whole initiation of the
social thing, talking and
trying to strategize, that's
going to kill me.
>> Okay, ask people questions,
because they love to talk about
themselves.
>> I'm definitely worried about
the social aspect.
I need to pay more attention to
that, so I need to do a little
bit more hustling.
Hopefully, pull out the
challenges and make them love
me.
>> The heavens unzipped on us.
>> Where we put the shelter is
very important, and this was,
obviously, a temporary thing.
>> Yeah, this, obviously...
>> It was a terrible idea.
>> What do y'all want to do?
>> Build a shelter.
>> Yeah, what do you want?
Here, here, up there?
Last night was really wet.
It's a reality check for these
guys up here.
We'll try to straighten this
mess up a little bit.
Maybe everybody will come
together today, you know.
>> There you go.
>> Yeah!
>> Does someone want to find
stuff with me?
>> What are you going to do?
>> I'm going to find, like,
some leaves.
>> I think we need fronds and
vines.
>> I'm not feeling so good.
My first night was pretty rough.
I was soaking wet for the whole
night.
I think I'm pretty sick.
I have chills, like, really bad.
And, like, I keep dry heaving.
Like I want to throw up but
there's just nothing in there.
>> What about Ashley?
She does not look good at all.
>> I feel so worried for her.
>> I've wrestled sick before.
I've wrestled with 104 fever
before.
I have to stay in the game.
I'm not leaving.
Hopefully, it will pass.
>> I know, if you're feeling
bad don't start thinking you're
on the block just because of
this.
Okay?
Ashley, I thought she'd be a
lot stronger person,
considering her profession and
how her demeanor is.
But if Ashley's health stays
the same, Ashley's going first.
>> We've got some tree mail.
Waa!
Dude, check this out.
>> You guys, we got some tree
mail.
>> Fei Long!
>> You guys, check out how
cool, eh.
>> "The untested enemy you must
face today.
They may have the power to send
one of you away.
With your namesake held above
you, and with honor in your
heart, will you lead your tribe
to victory or be the first one
to depart?"
This is immunity, obviously.
>> Obviously.
Game is on, huh?
>> That book, Art of War, we
should take a look at that
probably before our challenge.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
Chapter one, "The commander
stands for the general's
qualities of wisdom, sincerity,
benevolence, courage and
strictness."
>> In a way, it's saying we
need a commander, and I can't
help but notice that you've
kind of taken that position.
We do need someone who's
strong and knows how to take
lead, and you're very good at
it.
>> It feels weird, but, I think
I can do it.
>> Okay.
Aaron's a very strong player.
And I'm very, very smart in
trying to push the leader role
more so on to Aaron, because I
don't want to take that
position, but also to keep him
close to me.
I want him to trust me.
>> It will be like, a... it will
be like a democracy.
>> Yeah.
>> Being in the leadership
role, it's not someplace that I
want to be.
But leadership is just going
for it.
I'm ready, but I'm nervous.
>> "With your namesake held
above you, and with honor in
your heart, will you lead
your tribe to victory or be
the first one to depart?"
>> Ashley, you hanging in
there?
>> Yes, I'm going to pull
through.
>> If it's like obstacles, I
should be, probably... I'm
thinking I'm probably one of the
better guys.
I'm small, too, so it's easy
for me.
But climbing stuff isn't hard.
I'm a parkour and free-running
performer.
It is under control.
Parkour basically comes down to
what's the best, fastest, most
efficient, safest way to get
over anything.
So if there's a wall, you're
going to run up it, jump over
it.
If it there's rails, you're
going to bolt them.
Whatever it takes.
There we go, we've got it.
I'm going to use my skills to
do whatever I can to get my
team across the finish line
first and win.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
So, tell me about the first
three days.
Chicken, how has life been at
Zhan Hu?
>> About as well as expected.
(laughs)
Overall, we're doing okay.
We're okay.
>> PROBST: Jean-Robert, what's
the worst part?
>> The worst part, honestly,
Jeff, is just being fully
drenched and trying to sleep.
I haven't gotten a wink yet.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to your first
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, each tribe will be
tethered to and carrying a
ceremonial mascot that is both
awkward and heavy.
On my go, you must maneuver
through a series of obstacles.
When you get to the locked
gate, one tribe member will
race ahead and scale two walls,
releasing a drawbridge at each
wall.
You'll then retrieve a key,
race back, unlock the gate,
bring the rest of the tribe.
You must then make your way
through a swamp to the finish
platform, where you will need
to solve the puzzle.
Each tribe member must place
their pole in the correct spot.
The first tribe to do so wins
the challenge.
You want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes, please!
>> PROBST: The single most
important thing in this game is
immunity.
This is the immunity idol.
(cheers and applause)
When you have this in your
possession, you cannot be voted
out of this game.
Winning tribe gets immunity,
and winning tribe gets fire.
(applause)
Fire in the form of flint.
This will dramatically change
camp life.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: One more thing, you
were given your running shoes
for this challenge.
You can take them back to camp
with you.
(applause)
Take your spots.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
It is the first challenge of
Survivor: China.
At the head of the dragon and
retrieving the key for Fei Long
is James.
At the head of the tiger for
Zhan Hu, Frosti.
For immunity and fire,
survivors ready?
Go!
Denise falls for Fei Long.
Zhan Hu trying to figure it out.
We're dead even early on.
The tribe that works together
the best will win this
challenge.
Still dead even going up the
first platforms.
Fei Long in the lead with the
red dragon.
>> Up top.
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu slow going
with the yellow tiger.
Fei Long with a bit of a lead.
James got to unclip.
James having trouble getting
unclipped.
Zhan Hu is catching up.
>> Go, go!
>> PROBST: Frosti is now
unclipped.
So is James.
Both guys leap the first wall.
Frosti forgot to lower his
drawbridge.
He lost some time.
James now with a bit of a lead
for Fei Long.
Frosti right behind.
Got to unlock the gate and then
clip back in.
James has his lock open.
Frosti got it open.
Both are clipping in.
You've got to get clipped in.
We are neck and neck again.
Neck and neck going into the
swamp.
Got to stick together.
Zhan Hu struggling with the
yellow tiger.
Fei Long taking that red dragon
in the lead.
Fei Long first to the finish
platform.
Zhan Hu falling behind.
Zhan Hu now to the finish
platform.
>> Over here!
>> PROBST: You've got to put
your poles in the correct order.
They go in one way and only one
way.
Fei Long with some progress.
Zhan Hu getting nowhere with
the puzzle.
Fei Long thinks they have it.
Fei Long wins immunity and fire!
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Yeah!
Way to go, baby.
>> PROBST: Fei Long, immunity.
>> Yeah!
(applause)
>> PROBST: Nobody going home
tonight.
Denise wants the flint.
There's your fire.
Zhan Hu, you've got a date with
me, tribal council tonight,
where one of the eight of you
will earn the distinction of
being the first person voted
out of Survivor: China.
You have the afternoon to
figure it out.
See you at tribal.
>> I need to air out my shoes.
>> Full of mud.
>> I need to go have a seat down
there.
>> Have a seat, take a break.
You need five minutes?
Do what you got to do.
>> I need, like, more than that.
>> Take... hey, hey.
Let it all out.
Don't care if you cry.
Bawl your little head off, okay.
Don't sweat it.
As I see it right now, we are
all still a complete tribe.
I'd like to see us function as
such, pretty please.
We have unfortunate business to
do tonight.
It sucks.
It is a fact of life.
>> We need to all, like, really
pitch in at camp because I just
feel like, I know everybody is
doing stuff, and I just feel
like there's so much to do.
And it just sucks... like, it
sucks to know that, you know.
>> We are not going to win any
challenges if we don't have,
like, a decent shelter.
>> It is hard out here.
More so than I ever imagined.
And I'm trying to get through it
without being down about it.
We have to do two crossbeams
under like this.
We need two more of these
things.
What do you think is the best
way?
Do you think do it the same way
is the best way?
>> You need to get everybody's
opinion.
>> I'm asking your opinion.
>> I agree with you.
>> I wasn't stating my opinion.
I was asking yours.
>> I agree with you.
That'll work.
>> But I just, I say the two
options.
So which one do you think is
better in your opinion?
>> I would put two more pieces
down like you said.
>> I know you want to put two
more pieces, but how?
Chicken won't give an opinion
on how he thinks anything
should be done.
It's not worth anything to me
if he chooses not to apply his
strength.
We're going to try to keep the
instruments, if they're not in
use just in one area so
everybody knows where they are,
and, like, they don't get lost.
>> Peih-gee, all of a sudden,
she's sort of barking out
orders and trying to step into
this leadership position.
>> Take these two jugs and pour
them out into that big thing.
>> All righty.
>> If you're going to do that,
then you shouldn't be crying
after challenges.
You know, that's not a leader
role.
I know we have to work and
everything, but we still have
to think what we're going to do
at tribal council.
>> I would hope to think I'm
not going to be voted out by
anybody because I'm not sick at
all.
I feel a million times better
than I did before.
I see what can do.
I would hate to think one day
of being sick would dominate
over everything.
>> She was sick yesterday.
So....
>> That's not the point.
>> That's true.
>> I didn't ask if she was sick.
I just asked you what she done
yesterday.
Whether (inaudible), whether you
fell down the bank and sprained
you ankle, or you got a damn
headache, or whatever, it's an
ailment that can take you out of
the game.
It's just that, you know... it's
just that simple.
I feel like Ashley's gone.
That's what I'm writing down
tonight.
She ain't done nothing since
she's landed down here.
What are you doing?
You don't know?
>> I need to figure stuff out.
>> Whatever happens, happens.
You know, I don't even know if
I'm 100% safe tonight, you
know, for whatever reason.
That's what makes the element
of the game.
>> I think the heads on the
block tonight are Chicken,
Ashley, and Peih-gee.
Chicken, I, you know, we're the
two oldest guys.
And I've got nothing against
youth, but, you know in this
kind of environment situation,
I would prefer to have a little
more experience in our tribe
right now.
I don't wish anybody bad here.
But I want our tribe to be
strong.
And it's time to make stuff
happen.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach the flame.
This is part of the ritual of
tribal council because in this
game fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire, still
in the game; when your fire's
gone, so are you.
Let's talk about the first few
days.
Peih-gee, was this more than
you bargained for?
>> You know, I came in here
thinking this was a piece of
cake, but it is mud everywhere.
Trying to build a shelter is
hard because you don't have the
right implements.
>> PROBST: Chicken, you held up
two fingers.
>> It took us two days to do
that.
We should have had it by dark
the first day.
>> PROBST: Did you try to become
the leader and say, "Hey, let's
go, guys."
>> I'm not grabbing the bull by
the horns and done that, no, I
haven't.
But I guess somebody's going to
have to before we come together.
That's what's going to have to
be done.
>> PROBST: Show of hands--
anybody here willing to say
right now, "I will step up and
be the leader of this tribe?"
Well, you've got two, one man,
one woman.
>> We don't have time to mess
around.
I did not want to step in to
this position at all.
And you know what?
If I don't step up and kick
someone in the butt to do
something, I don't know what's
going to happen, but I will
step up and do what I can to
help get this tribe together
and proficient and then focus
on the challenges at hand, and
hopefully get it really nice
and tight.
>> PROBST: Peih-gee, you put
your hand up.
What would you bring as a
leader?
>> It is hard because you don't
want to be bossy.
These are grown people and I
don't want to be sitting around
trying to tell people what to
do, but on the other hand,
somebody has to kind of do it
if it's not happening naturally.
If you're just floundering
around, you're going to die out
here.
>> PROBST: So, did you guys just
make a decision, your first
tribe decision?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: But after tonight's
tribal council, there will only
be seven people left, so you're
probably wise to always be a
little concerned.
Okay, so made a little progress
as a tribe.
Now you have to make your first
big decision.
Who do you get rid of?
Dave, what does this tribe need
to do with tonight's vote to
make it a better tribe?
>> Trying to trim the
least-productive people out of
it.
>> PROBST: Chicken, what are you
going to base your vote on
tonight?
>> I'll base my vote on tonight
the person who has done the
least in the last three days.
It's just cut and dried.
>> PROBST: Erik, how important
is it whether somebody is
pulling their weight or not
pulling their weight?
>> I think contributions is
huge.
I mean, especially now that
we've realized how long it
takes to build a shelter.
And so I think we're going to
really have to hold each other
accountable.
>> PROBST: Ashley, think you're
fitting in with this group?
>> I did for a while.
And I mean, now that I'm
hearing everybody speak freely,
I kind of feel like that if you
broke it down per day, I was
throwing up, I was laying on
the ground.
I pretty much was feeling like
I was going to die.
And I guess if you put that in
the equation, then I would
have technically been the one
who has done the least amount
of work.
I don't feel like I should be
judged on that.
>> PROBST: So you're feeling a
little uneasy.
>> Right now I am because I
hear how they're talking.
>> PROBST: Chicken, how do you
think you're fitting?
>> I don't fit in.
You know, I don't.
But, I'm not the one that's
done the least amount of work,
and you're out there in the
middle of a jungle.
You ain't got nothing.
So do you want the guy that
don't fit in or do you want the
guy that works?
You know, if we don't open our
eyes, we going to be seeing you
a lot.
>> PROBST: Okay, so, it sounds
like you have a plan to have
leadership in your tribe.
Now you have to make the first
big decision-- who to get rid
of.
It is time to vote.
Frosti, you're up.
>> I'm voting for Peih-gee
because I feel like the group
already has a leader, and
that's Dave.
>> Just bad luck.
Wrong time, wrong place.
>> Chicken, I think you've
truly lived up to your
nickname.
You've been too afraid to step
up to anything, and we don't
need that right now.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Chicken.
Ashley.
Two votes Ashley, one vote
Chicken.
Peih-gee.
There's two votes Chicken, two
vote Ashley, one vote Peih-gee.
Chicken.
There's three votes Chicken,
two votes Ashley, one vote
Peih-gee.
First person voted out of
Survivor: China-- Chicken.
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Chicken, the tribe has spoken.
>> I heard 'em.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
Well, if there's one good thing
about coming to tribal council
tonight, you will go back to
camp with your torches, which
means you will have fire.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> PROBST: Here's flint.
>> Yes!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
At Fei Long, the poker player's
bluff is called.
>> Jean-Robert, you need to
start pulling your weight.
>> Why don't we all rest?
>> PROBST: Dave takes command
at Zhan Hu.
>> You're the leader and I'll
let you do what you want.
>> How many fires have you
built, sweetheart?
If she want to fight, I can
give her a fight.
>> PROBST: And the pro wrestler
comes out in Ashley.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> It was kind of a shock that
the young group didn't come
together, and I don't think
they ever will.
They're just playing by the
seat of their pants.
I put a lot of thought going
into it but I never got nowhere.
There's no one more proud to be
such a small part of one
big adventure.
It was truly an honor to be
here.
Without a doubt.