>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor...
James found the second hidden
immunity idol at Zhan Hu.
>> I have it now.
I have it in my possession.
I'm on Survivor with two idols.
>> JEFF: Erik found the plaque
James discarded, and Jaime
suspected it might be an
immunity idol.
>> If I play the hidden immunity
idol tonight, it's probably
going to shock everyone.
I'm not as dumb as I look, and
maybe they're figuring it out.
>> JEFF: The next day, the two
tribes merged...
Drop your buffs.
You are merged.
...and enjoyed a celebration
feast.
>> Sweet and sour pork, you
guys.
>> Beef.
>> Whoa!
Easy!
>> Jeff's here!
>> JEFF: What up?
In an unexpected challenge...
You will be tested on your
recollection of events that
happened during the feast and
the celebration.
Frosti was the first to win
individual immunity.
The former Zhan Hu were
outnumbered by the former Fei
Long.
>> Now all we have to do is put
the nails in the coffin and bury
them.
>> JEFF: Convinced they had a
hidden idol, Jaime and Erik
planned to use it to get rid of
Jean-Robert.
>> JEFF: At tribal council,
I-/////!ll read the votes.
Jaime played the idol while a
shocked Jean-Robert looked on.
The rules of Survivor state if
the immunity idol is played, any
votes cast against that person
will not count, and the person
with the next highest number of
votes will be sent home.
This, however, is not a hidden
immunity idol.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> JEFF: Jaime, Erik, and Peih-
Gee voted for Jean-Robert.
But the former members of Fei
Long stuck together, and Jaime
became the first member of the
jury.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I know.
I was, like, terrified.
I was like, "Oh, my gosh."
>> I mean, I knew 100% I'm going
home.
At tribal council, I had a close
call.
Jaime pulled this little plaque
out of her bag.
I mean, I was like, "Is this
really happening?
Could this possibly be that she
found an individual immunity
idol somewhere in our camp?"
>> Before you get in bed, Erik
has to go back there.
>> Well, just move over!
Move over.
What the hell?
Well, goodness gracious, sakes
alive.
>> You wouldn't want to move.
So shut up, James.
( laughter )
>> Jean Robert don't know that I
have both immunity idols.
We can't tell him that, because
it's Jean-Robert.
He's going to mess something up.
We just need to keep his dumb
ass in line just because we're
stuck with him now.
We need his vote, so we have to
deal with it.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> I'm back with my original
tribemates, and we have to stick
together.
We put ourselves in a position
by all these personalities
coming together.
We're complete opposites.
I mean we've got a lunch lady,
we have a professional gambler,
we have a stewardess,
We have a waitress from New
York.
There's a gravedigger.
All our personalities, even
though we clash, we pull
together, and we've won
together, you know?
And the other team, that's not
how they work.
The other team, they got
together as a clique.
They're not trying to win a
million dollars.
They were trying to win the high
school friend contest.
I just got two of them, because
they're catching too fast.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Wow!
>> That is beautiful!
At this moment, James is in a
very good position, because he
has both immunity idols for
sure, so he's almost guaranteed
himself in a top five position
right now.
He's a strong physical, mental
player of this game.
So I am kind of afraid that he
could win the whole thing.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
So you guys ready to get to your
reward challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: For today's challenge,
you will be divided into two
teams of four.
One member from each team will
sit in their boat while the
opposing team will use buckets
of water to try and sink them.
The person in the boat will have
to bail the water out as fast as
possible to stay afloat.
The first team to sink the other
team's boat two times wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, please.
>> JEFF: The winning team of
four will leave here and be
taken to an ancient village.
People have lived here for the
past 1,000 years.
It's a beautiful place where
you'll enjoy an authentic
Chinese meal.
>> Oh!
>> JEFF: It's a break from camp
and a chance to put something
good in your belly.
>> Hell, yeah.
>> JEFF: In addition, the
winning team of four will take
this with them to open on the
reward.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: All right, we're going
to randomly choose captains.
We'll do a schoolyard pick.
Peih-Gee, you're the captain of
the Red Team.
Jean-Robert, you're the captain
of the Yellow Team.
You won the right to choose
first.
Who do you want?
>> Hang on, let me think about
this first.
All right, I'll take James.
>> JEFF: Jean-Robert takes
James.
Peih-Gee, who are you going to
pick?
>> Frosti.
>> JEFF: Frosti joins Peih-Gee.
James, it is now your selection.
>> Todd.
>> JEFF: James chooses Todd.
>> Frosti, it's now your pick,
who do you want?
>> I guess I'll go with Erik.
>> JEFF: We are right back where
we started-- three Fei Long
members, three Zhan Hu members.
Todd who do you want?
>> I-/////!ll take Amanda.
>> JEFF: Amanda finishes out the
Yellow Team.
Erik, you have one choice to
make-- it is between Denise and
Courtney.
Who will be the final person
participating in this challenge?
>> We're going to go with
Courtney because she's light.
>> JEFF: Courtney.
>> Sorry, Denise.
>> That's all right.
>> JEFF: Take a spot along with
Erik, Frosti, and Peih-Gee on
team red.
Denise, you will not participate
in this challenge.
You'll not be eligible for the
reward.
Take a spot on the bench.
>> Sorry.
>> JEFF: All right, I'll give
you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, this challenge plays
best two out of three.
Each round you'll put somebody
different in the boat.
For the first round, who's going
to be in the boat?
>> I am.
>> JEFF: Todd and Courtney.
Get in the boat.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Using buckets to get water to
sink the other team's boat...
>> Come on, Courtney.
Come here, Courtney.
>> ...while the person in the
boat paddles away, trying to
avoid you.
>> Come on, Courtney!
>> I hate you!
I hate you all!
>> JEFF: Courtney getting
drenched right away by Amanda,
James, and Jean-Robert.
>> I hate all of you!
>> JEFF: She's baling as fast as
she can.
Todd getting drenched by Frosti,
Erik, and Peih-Gee.
He's trying to bail.
Courtney taking on more water
from James and Amanda.
She's got to get away from them.
>> Oh, Jeff, shut up!
>> Get in the middle, Courtney,
get in the middle.
>> I'm trying.
>> JEFF: Todd doing a good job
staying in the middle, making
his boat a hard target, and
bailing at the same time.
Amanda just dumping water in
Courtney's boat.
Todd in very good shape.
Frosti, Erik, and Peih-Gee
having to chase him all over the
place.
Courtney taking on a lot of
water.
Very close to going under.
Todd has hardly any water at all
in his boat.
James, Amanda, Jean-Robert
having no mercy.
>> There goes Courtney.
>> JEFF: Uh-oh.
That will do it.
Jean-Robert, James, Amanda, and
Todd win the first round.
All right, Amanda going in the
boat for the yellow team in
round two.
Frosti's going in the boat for
the red team in round two.
Yellow leads, one-zip.
First to two wins reward.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Amanda in the boat for yellow.
Frosti in the boat for red.
Will the red team have better
luck this round?
Now it's Jean-Robert, Todd, and
James trying to sink Frosti.
It's Peih-Gee, Erik, and
Courtney trying to sink Amanda.
A trip to an ancient village and
a nice meal on the line.
Jean-Robert, James, and Todd
doing a good job on Frosti.
Amanda's got a nice, safe spot
in the middle, making herself a
hard target.
Peih-Gee, Courtney look tired
already.
James not tired at all.
Scoop after scoop after scoop.
Frosti in trouble now.
He's cornered.
Frosti, you've got to get out of
there, man!
Frosti is sunk!
Yellow team wins!
Amanda, Jean-Robert, James, and
Todd going on reward.
All right, Frosti, Peih-Gee,
Courtney, Erik, and Denise, got
nothing for you.
Get in the boat and head back to
camp.
James, Todd, Amanda, Jean-
Robert, you're going to leave
here.
You'll be taken to an ancient
village.
You'll have a nice meal.
While you're there, open this,
read it together.
It is for all four of you.
Jean-Robert, catch.
Have a good time.
>> Thank you.
>> This is amazing.
>> How cool, eh?
>> The reward was nice.
We had the opportunity to go and
see a thousand-year-old village.
Now, I mean, I'm not really one
to enjoy the romantic side of
stuff, but when you walk in the
place, the construction of
everything, and you could feel,
like, the history, that was
really nice.
>> Guys, where are we?
Like, oh, my god, this is
unbelievable.
>> This is authentic Chinese
dining.
This is the real deal.
Wow.
>> Idol clue.
There is a hidden immunity idol.
Wow.
>> Really?
>> All right, here we go.
"This is the final clue to the
whereabouts of hidden immunity."
I've got to tell you, when I
read this, I was, like, a little
bit surprised.
As much information as there has
been out there, I should have
known something.
I should have had some sort of
clue.
I mean, that shook me up a
little bit.
"Hidden immunity idol clue
number one-- what is thought to
be hidden may sometimes be seen.
>> When Jean-Robert busted open
those clues for the hidden
immunity idol, it was kind of
funny, because there's no idol
out there.
It's already been found.
James has both immunity idols,
and Jean-Robert is the only one
from Fei Long who doesn't know
about it.
>> This is big, guys.
I mean, winning today's
challenge...
>> Exactly.
>> Bigger than dinner and
culture.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Oh!
>> Mmm!
>> Wonderful, yes!
>> Oh, there's more coming,
still.
>> Yeah!
>> Wow, wontons are great.
>> Yeah.
>> James, you think they know
how to make wontons here?
>> I do believe.
This place has been here a
thousand years.
I think they might have made a
wonton or two.
What you think?
Hand me them peanuts.
>> This is the best day ever.
>> Everybody made the perfect
picks.
>> So, what do you do with that
afterwards?
Where do you store it?
What do you do?
You had it before.
What did you do with it?
>> It disappeared.
>> Oh, it disappears.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm not bringing that back.
Are you bringing it back?
>> Hell, no.
>> Well, you better jog your
memory, homey.
>> I did not know there was an
American immunity idol.
>> American immunity idol.
Cool.
That's great.
There's an American immunity
idol.
>> We could really have some fun
with this, you guys.
Jean-Robert has no idea.
I think that was the best part
of the whole evening was hearing
him talk about finding this
idol-- "What do you guys think
it can be?
I don't know where it is."
>> Guys, I've been drinking wine
all right?
American immunity idol.
>> I'm very upset right now.
You know, what am I going to do,
though?
I mean, there was a pick today
at the challenge.
I mean, I was standing there,
you know, looking at everybody,
and just sitting on the bench.
And, you know, I'm big, I'm fat,
I'm always the last one picked.
I mean, it's been like that my
whole life.
And here it is again.
You know, I mean, you're the
last one standing there.
Are they going to do that when
it comes down to the final
seven?
Am I going to be the one that's
going to go home before J.R?
Am I going to be one that goes
home before James?
I don't want to be that person.
You know, I want to stay in this
game as long as I possibly can.
>> I guess, you know, James is
probably a bigger threat.
>> No, J.R. is a major threat.
>> I want J.R.
I think he's kind of more of the
full threat package.
>> There's five of us here.
I'm, like, "Wait a minute."
I was like, "If we all band
together, it will be four to
five, and guess what?"
Jean-Robert and James, oh,
Amanda, okay, bye.
I kind of have nothing to lose.
Like, I'll try anything at this
point.
You know, if J.R. goes out
before I do, if either you or
Courtney are on final two, I'll
give either one of you my vote.
Because I would love to see him
taken out before me.
>> Peih-Gee is trying to shake
things up and get us to vote out
Jean-Robert.
Nobody likes him, so it's kind
of an easy vote.
If I decide to go with Peih-Gee
and Erik, I could end up in a
good situation with them, but I
don't want to go against the
rest of the tribe and have them
vote against me.
So I'm thinking it over and
deciding what I'm going to do.
If I think the best way for me
is to go with you guys, then I'm
going to go with you guys.
If I think the best way for me
is to go with them, then I'm
going to go with them.
I'm going to tell you that
honestly,
Straight up.
>> I didn't even sleep last
night, I was so anxious to get
that immunity idol.
I mean, that's the difference in
the game.
That could protect me.
That could be my million
dollars right there.
I looked around, and I remember
some clue about four bats, and I
know it's above, and I got the
feeling that it was someplace
where we walk every time we come
home.
So I decided it was probably
one of those mini pagodas.
Now I'm thinking it might be one
of these plaques.
The four bats thing makes sense,
one of the plaques.
So right now I think I'm going
to try to take the other three
down, and I can figure out which
one of them is right.
If I have the immunity idol, it
gives me a trump card.
I like the direction I'm going,
but I feel more comfortable with
the trump card in my pocket
knowing that the general public
doesn't have access to it right
now.
>> James, you eat a good one-
fourth of what's in there.
>> Oh, I do.
>> You average probably two and
a half times the average person.
>> I'm not like you.
I'm not laying down...
>> No, no, no, don't say like
me.
When you were gone I was out
there fishing and I never ate
more than my fair portion, okay?
Please don't say like me.
>> We have been in the jungle
for 23 days now, and these
people are driving me insane.
I hate hearing Jean-Robert's
voice.
I hate hearing James complain
how he's so hungry.
Plus it kind of pisses me off
that James has both hidden
immunity idols, being that I
found it and told him where the
other one was, and he hasn't
even offered to give one back.
That drives me insane.
So I would love to see some
craziness happen here at camp.
>> James, he's got himself in a
great position.
With that hidden immunity idol,
he's guaranteed in the final
four.
You know it.
Yeah, people would be like, "You
played a great game James.
You did fantastic, here you go."
What if he keeps winning,
winning, idol, idol?
Hell, no am I messing with two
idols like that.
If James doesn't win immunity,
he might have to go.
If he's guaranteed that Peih-Gee
is going, he won't play that
idol.
>> The plan was originally to
get rid of Peih-Gee next, and
then Erik and Frosti after that.
Now, all of a sudden, Todd is in
a big hurry to get rid of James,
and him changing so quickly,
like, really makes me nervous.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> And...
We will not tell Peih-Gee.
>> All right.
>> Because we can't, because she
will tell James.
>> In this game, you've got to
take advantage of whatever
happens whenever you can.
And right now, people are
starting to view me as a swing
vote, which ends up being not so
bad.
>> Sound good?
Sounds good.
>> I'm always looking for a
chance to make sure that I'm
safe, so right now, the plan is
to not let James win immunity at
this next challenge and
blindside him at tribal tonight.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: First things first.
Frosti, you mind bringing it
over?
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you are
going to balance on a large
barrel that is filled with
water.
There is a hole on the bottom of
the barrel.
As the water drains out, it will
become more and more unstable,
making it more difficult to keep
your balance.
When you fall off, you're out.
Last person left sitting on
their barrel wins immunity, is
guaranteed a one in eight shot
at a million dollars.
We've already drawn for
positions.
Take your spots.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
Everybody sit up straight.
First lever you're going to push
is the yellow lever.
That will pull the plug,
allowing the water to drain out
of your barrel.
Three, two, one, push.
Now, push the red one forward.
Keep in mind, when you push the
red one forward, your barrel is
now not locked anymore.
Three, two, one, push.
This challenge is underway.
Water draining out of
everybody's barrel.
Everybody's barrel is unlocked
and moving.
The only rules are your hands
and your feet can only touch
your barrel.
You cannot touch any part of the
structure in front of or behind
your barrel.
>> I don't think mine's balanced
properly, Jeff.
>> JEFF: Glad you're still
around, Jean-Robert.
Always need a complainer.
>> I thought I was the
complainer.
>> Whoa, whoa!
This sucks.
>> JEFF: James struggling a
little bit.
Denise wobbling just a little
bit.
Courtney is like a statue.
>> Oh, man, I got an itch.
None of you guys are itching?
Your heads don't itch, anybody?
Those mosquito bites from last
night.
>> Shut up.
>> Bitch.
>> JEFF: James struggling.
Does a good job of recovering.
Jean-Robert playing around.
And it could cost him and it
does.
Jean-Robert's the first one out.
Take a spot on the bench.
Eight people left.
Denise really fighting it, and
Denise goes in the swamp.
Denise the second person out of
the challenge.
We are down to seven people
left.
Immunity on the line.
>> Whoa.
Gotcha.
>> JEFF: James struggling.
>> Whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
Whoa.
Come on.
>> JEFF: another good save by
James.
It is hot out here.
You've been on your barrels for
over 20 minutes now.
>> Oh, geez.
>> JEFF: Erik with a nice
recovery.
Peih-Gee shows the first sign of
trouble.
Courtney still looking solid.
James struggling again.
Can he make another recovery?
No.
James is the third person out of
this challenge.
>> ♪ Don don don... ♪
>> JEFF: Take a spot on the
bench.
We are down to six people left
in this challenge.
Todd starting to struggle a bit
now.
Erik struggling.
Can he get it back?
And Erik goes in.
Erik is the fourth person out of
this challenge.
Peih-Gee and Amanda struggling a
bit.
Peih-Gee fighting it, and loses
the battle.
Peih-Gee is the fifth person out
of this challenge.
Whoa, Amanda, hands off.
Amanda's out.
Touched the structure.
Amanda is the sixth person out
of the challenge.
We are down to three-- Courtney,
Frosti, Todd.
All fighting for immunity.
>> ♪ Starving artist
on the dragon ♪
>> Frosti's singing.
>> ♪ Balancing on barrels
for Jeff Probst ♪
>> JEFF: Todd is the seventh
person out of this challenge.
And then there were two.
>> Lovers.
>> JEFF: Courtney and Frosti
sitting side by side.
Courtney has not moved in 32
minutes.
>> I am lazy.
>> That sucks.
That sucks.
Oh... no, never mind.
>> JEFF: Frosti tries to
recover.
Can't do it.
Frosti's out.
Courtney wins immunity!
>> Thanks, guys.
>> JEFF: Courtney, come on over.
>> It's almost like a pageant.
>> Good job, Courtney.
>> JEFF: Courtney, you are safe
tonight at tribal council.
With this around your neck, you
cannot be voted out.
Courtney has a one in eight shot
at a million dollars.
For the rest of you, tonight,
one of you going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Thank you.
I did win immunity today.
I didn't think I would ever win
anything.
( laughs )
So I pretty much don't care at
this point who gets voted out.
I'm immune tonight, so can't get
me.
Nope.
>> I was crushed I didn't win it
today, because I know I'm next
on the chopping block.
I've been really trying to
scramble and save my ass, and
Denise seemed really open to the
idea of voting with me and my
other allies.
So hopefully it will get me
through one more tribal council.
>> I thought you were on the
chopping block because you were
getting votes.
>> Actually, right now I might
not get as many votes.
>> Things have changed?
>> I think they... yeah.
I... I have the hidden immunity
idol.
Yeah.
Now that I have it, I look like
I'm pretty much guaranteed top
five for sure right now.
>> I was trying to think, how
can I keep me in the game
longer, and then Jean-Robert
told me he had the idol, and
that changed everything.
'Cause I'm 99% positive that
James has it.
What would you say if I told you
I was pretty sure that you
didn't have the right immunity
idol?
>> I'd say that you probably
don't have as many clues as I
do.
>> Okay, I'm willing to share
with you what I know.
>> Okay.
>> James comes over to our camp,
and that little block from the
archway, we looked in James' bag
and there were two of them.
>> But...
>> Because there's two hidden
immunity idols.
>> There's two hidden immunity
idols?
>> One in each camp.
And I'm almost positive James
has them.
Okay.
Hmmm.
How sick is that?
And this is the guy who is
favored to win every challenge
from here out.
I'll tell what you we can do.
We'll keep this on the DL.
>> Have you been looking?
What have you come up with?
>> What I came up with is the
realization that you're holding
out on me.
That's what I came up with.
>> I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
>> Yes, you do.
>> No, I don't.
You had to know I was going to
figure it out sooner or later.
>> Figure what out?
>> You have two immunity idols.
Two of them, and you can't tell
your boy?
Nobody told me, bro.
Who else do you think would
figure something out like that
except for me?
Come on.
Okay.
>> Jean-Robert was just fishing
for answers.
I don't know what he was trying
to pull.
He knows I don't like being
sequestered or cornered, like he
was so cunning he'd fool me in
some way.
>> Now I'm not even going to ask
you anymore.
I'm telling you that I already
know, and I'm leaving it up to
you to decide-- do you want to
work with me or are we going on
our own?
The best course to the end is
always going to be with me,
not against me.
It cannot work up on the well
with you if you don't go with
me.
>> I might look like a dumb
monkey, and just fall for
anything, but I'm really not.
I mean, come on, dude.
You're Jean-Robert.
You can't trust anything that
comes out of your mouth anyway.
Why would I align with you?
That would be the worst move of
Survivor history to align with
that guy.
>> James kept playing dumb like
he doesn't know what I was
talking about, and he didn't
make any kind of offer about
what we could do with this
advantage together.
Now I feel like it's kind of
fair game.
Big, big news.
>> I know where the idol is, and
there's not just one idol.
There's two idols.
>> You're talking about James,
right?
>> He has both idols.
>> Okay.
>> How did you know that?
>> I was just... I've heard
hearsay.
>> He has both idols.
Here's the thing-- we could
blindside him tonight, because
he will not pull out the idol
tonight.
>> I know, I know.
Let's see how it goes today.
You know, it's really funny-- I
had an original idea to take
James out, and then Jean-Robert
just came up with the same idea,
and I was kind of bothered by
the fact that he's coming up
with all these ideas I've had
for days now.
So I'm always entertaining
options.
I could change my mind in two
minutes.
Who knows?
This game is fun, and I like
keeping it fun.
>> He right now has Erik and
possibly Peih-Gee and Frosti.
That's four.
And I'm five.
He thinks you're going tonight.
I played it up.
Like, "Yeah, okay, this sounds
like a good idea."
But should we do Jean-Robert
tonight?
We don't want to tell Denise or
no?
>> No.
Denise wavering, and Denise
getting pissed off.
>> I still think we should get
rid of Peih-Gee tonight and the
Jean-Robert next time.
Todd is all over the place right
now.
One person comes up to him, he
rethinks his whole strategy.
He's second-guessing himself.
And in this game, you have to be
confident about your choices.
So I really don't know what's
going to happen at this point.
>> Here's Courtney.
>> Courtney, come here.
>> Um...
I don't know.
I mean... I don't know.
I mean... well, I don't... it's
up to you guys.
I don't give a crap.
I'm not entirely sure what
happened, but all of a sudden,
Todd decided to vote for Jean-
Robert.
>> I think our best bet is Jean-
Robert tonight.
>> It's a widely known fact that
Jean-Robert and I have hated
each other since day one.
So if everyone's finally willing
to vote him out, then great.
But he's become the Susan Lucci
of tribal council.
Like, his name is always up
there, but he never quite gets
voted out.
So I don't have much faith that
it will actually happen.
>> I knew Jean-Robert was going
to try something, and I'm just
going to have to deal with it.
Hopefully I'll make it through.
I don't know if I will take the
idols with me, because I
shouldn't have to use them.
So I might just roll the dice
tonight.
As long as I make it to the next
one, I should be all right.
But, I mean, you never know.
>> JEFF: I'll now bring in the
first member of our jury.
Jaime, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Just remind you the jury is here
to observe, not to interact.
Courtney, would you have ever
guessed that you would be here
on day 24 wearing the immunity
necklace?
>> Hell no!
( applause )
But if I was going to win a
challenge, you better believe it
was one that involved not
falling in the swamp.
>> JEFF: James, this is the
second tribal council you've
been at without immunity.
You're one of the biggest
physical threats in this game.
Do you get more concerned with
each tribal that maybe tonight
is your night?
>> Yes, I do.
I am the biggest physical threat
but the far greater threats are
the talkers, the ones who could
form alliances easier, that
would trade up and switch around
and do all kinds of other stuff.
>> JEFF: Peih-Gee, if you look
at the tribe tonight, you still
have a great number of Fei Long
members, and you have you,
Frosti, and Erik.
>> Yeah, Erik and I are the only
ones that brought our stuff, so,
obviously, I think we're the
only ones who think that we're
going home.
You know, like, I was devastated
losing that challenge today, and
it's tough.
It's really hard.
>> JEFF: Jean-Robert, how
frustrated would you be if the
situation were reversed and you
were sitting in Peih-Gee's or
Erik's shoes?
>> I would be really frustrated,
because they're this a really
bad position right now, really
bad position.
I mean, they've had really bad
cards thrown at them.
They basically got the deuce-
seven off suit in a no limit
game.
And they've come in a situation,
it's pretty much have
inevitable.
>> JEFF: Erik, agree with Jean-
Robert, disagree?
>> It's, of course, tough, but
everybody else that's left from
Fei Long is going to realize,
like, if I have six people,
somebody's at the bottom of
that, and I'm not just saying
that to lobby.
I'm just saying, like, if I know
I'm going to go fifth or sixth,
I'm going to start thinking
before that.
And I'm not saying that to try
and sell people.
That is how this game has to
work.
People are going to have to
split.
>> JEFF: James you're throwing
your hands up.
>> I mean, he's so cute what he
says like he's trying to play it
up.
But I like... I like it.
He's beautiful.
He's working it.
He's working it right now.
Already.
>> JEFF: Jean-Robert, at the
last tribal council, Jaime
played what she thought was a
hidden immunity idol.
How does the notion that there
could be a hidden immunity idol
change the game?
>> When Jaime presented that
last week, I thought I was going
home.
When your job is being the local
jerk...
( laughter )
...as the local jerk, I will
probably have my name on a
ballot or two maybe three every
time.
But if somebody happens to place
that idol at the right time,
that could be me going home.
That's scary.
>> JEFF: Amanda, is it true that
every time you come to tribal
you truly believe it could be
you?
>> Every time you come here, you
expect to be going because,
anybody could be doing things
that you don't know about.
So I don't like coming to tribal
council, and I'm not
comfortable.
I'm not.
>> JEFF: Okay, Courtney, you
have individual immunity.
As always, if you want to give
it up to somebody else, you can.
>> No.
Screw you guys.
>> JEFF: Courtney's going to
keep it.
You cannot vote for Courtney.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Todd, you're up.
>> I hope this is the last time
I have to vote for you.
Maybe we all can sleep now.
>> Peih-Gee, I'm voting for you.
You just happened to get on the
wrong tribe.
>> You've played an incredible
game, my friend.
That's why we've got to send you
packing.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
If anyone has a hidden immunity
idol, now is the time to play
it.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jean-Robert.
Jean-Robert.
Two votes Jean-Robert.
Peih-Gee.
Two votes Jean-Robert, one vote
James.
Peih-Gee, one vote James.
That's two votes James, two
votes Jean-Robert.
One vote Peih-Gee.
James.
That's three votes James, two
votes Jean-Robert, one vote
Peih-Gee.
Jean-Robert.
We're tied.
Three votes Jean-Robert, three
votes James, one vote Peih-Gee.
Jean-Robert.
That's four votes Jean-Robert.
Three votes James, one vote
Peih-Gee, one vote left.
Eighth person voted out and the
second member of our jury, Jean-
Robert.
You need to bring me your torch.
Jean-Robert, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, I think tonight's vote
speaks for itself.
Tribal lines are gone.
This is a brand-new game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
>> I'm stuck in a jungle with
people that I don't like.
>> JEFF: Tension rises at Hae Da
Fung.
>> What I'm saying is...
>> Blame.
>> Can I finish?
>> JEFF: And a surprise at
tribal council.
Tonight you will not be heading
directly back to camp.
We have more business to attend
to here.
>> I really loved the way I
played this game.
If I were to relate what
happened to a game of poker, I
pushed all in and it didn't work
out for me.
But I'm playing for first, and
the only person who really
threatened that first-place
position for me was James.
But I think they realized that I
probably was the best player in
the game, and they would feel a
lot more comfortable with me out
of the game.