>> JEFF PROBST: Tonight, on a
special episode of Survivor:
China, we'll take a closer look
at how the final seven survivors
made it deep into the game.
Todd.
>> I'm smaller than the rest of
our people, but I'm quick and
I'm smart.
>> PROBST: Courtney.
>> My strength is that I'm not a
strong player.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee.
>> I'm going to come off as a
bitch and I'm going to come off
as bossy.
>> PROBST: Erik.
>> Unless I'm way off, I haven't
made any enemies.
>> PROBST: Denise.
>> I want to stay in this game
as long as I possibly can.
>> PROBST: Amanda.
>> I try hard.
I'm athletic.
I am a huge threat in this game.
>> PROBST: And James.
>> I really would love to see
how these people would be
without me being here.
It would be hilarious.
Because they honestly would be
dead.
>> Watch your mouth, dude.
Word gets around.
>> Todd, when you come
confronting me, make sure you
know what you're talking about.
>> PROBST: We'll also see how
their stories unfolded...
>> Bottoms up, baby.
>> PROBST: ...with 14 scenes of
all new footage.
>> I ate the legs and a little
bit of the ass and now I'm
craving frog.
>> If we lose, you're going
home.
>> My impression of Jaime.
>> Oh, my god.
>> If you're not in the mood to
accept my apology, that's fine.
>> No.
I know what kind of person you
are.
>> James...
>> PROBST: New twists constantly
reshaped the game...
Fei Long, you now get to kidnap
one member of their tribe.
...into one of the most
unpredictable Survivors ever.
And for the first time ever, one
castaway holds two immunity
idols...
>> I cannot stop smiling,
because I'm not going anywhere.
It's all good, baby.
>> PROBST: ...making him
virtually invincible.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> PROBST: 27 days ago, 16
Americans traveled to a remote
section of rural China for the
adventure of a lifetime.
Their journey got off to a
grueling start.
>> We don't know how many more
stairs there are.
>> Have mercy.
>> Goodness.
>> I don't see the end.
>> Guys, it's a long way to go.
>> We got to the temple, I mean,
it was hard.
We are carrying bags up 450
stairs and we figured, "Oh, this
is it.
We're ready to start this thing
up."
>> We should build shelter right
here.
>> More stairs?
We're just climbing up these
really steep stairs.
And every time they curved
around, and every time we
thought we were there, it's
another curve, and another
curve.
>> I'm telling you guys, ain't
no money at the top of this
hill.
You might as well slow down.
We'll go another ten.
>> All the young kids, they're
all, like, grabbing their stuff,
running up the hills.
The big guys have got them over
their heads and they're walking
up.
I got stuck with Chicken.
He's like, "Take it slow.
You don't have been to rush.
Ten at a time.
We're going to do ten this
time."
And he'd stop and sit down and
wipe his brow.
I'm like, "All right, I'm going
to hang with this dude for a
while."
>> Thank you.
>> Welcome to China.
( applause )
>> I was, like, looking at my
outfit.
I was uncomfortable and I was
embarrassed.
It's definitely not appropriate
for a temple.
>> Come on, girls.
Cover up the boobies for temple.
>> The Buddhist monks actually
came over and gave us drapes.
Almost all the girls had to use
drapes over their dresses.
I'm sure they don't get a whole
lot of skimpy dresses in the
temple.
>> PROBST: During the Buddhist
welcoming ceremony Leslie had a
moral dilemma.
>> I'm a believer in Jesus
Christ, and in the bible it
says, "Thou shall not bow down
to any other god."
You know, it really felt like
worship, and I just couldn't do
it.
>> PROBST: When the ceremony
ended, the survivors were split
into two tribes.
Yellow tribe, your name is Zhan
Hu, which means "Fighting
Tiger."
Red tribe, your name is Fei
Long-- it means "Flying Dragon."
All right, good luck, guys.
>> Thanks so much.
>> PROBST: After settling into
camp, Todd nominated Aaron to be
the leader of Fei Long.
>> We do need someone who's
strong and knows how to take
lead, and you're very good at
it.
>> It feels weird, but I can...
I think I can did it.
>> I am very, very smart in
trying to push the leader role
more so on to Aaron.
>> PROBST: While over at Zhan
Hu, Chicken's assertiveness was
squashed.
>> You think this here is going
to hold up?
>> We have to build something,
though, so let's stop being
negative.
>> I was just giving my opinion
and nobody wanted it, so I'm
done suggesting.
>> PROBST: After three days of
intense hunger, Zhan Hu resorted
to eating anything they could
get their hands on.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Just don't stare at it.
>> Just squeeze.
>> It's like popping a big,
nasty zit.
>> Eww!
That's disgusting, Erik.
>> Dude, I'm hungry.
We weren't find any plants we
could eat that were edible, and
we couldn't get the fire, so no
rice, so there was nothing.
I was just ready to eat
something.
>> You know, that's TMI, man,
milking worms.
>> Milking worm poo.
>> I'm, like, sitting here, we
squeezing poop out of worms, and
making people eat them, but I
think they'll be glad they
pushed the boundaries, and I
think that's the key to
surviving out here.
>> Shoot it!
>> I'm hard core.
>> Whoo!
>> Ching.
>> I'm doing three big guys
here.
>> Oh, just... ah!
>> Do it.
>> Whoo!
>> Ew!
>> Oh!
>> We're still living so
primitively.
Nothing to eat.
We're drinking dirty rain.
Bugs.
You know, they're eating worms.
I mean, it's just gross.
It's just filthy.
It's disgusting.
>> Oh, yeah, that wasn't bad at
all.
>> See?
>> I could do another one.
>> PROBST: But worms weren't the
only strange foods the tribes
ate.
>> Oh, my god.
Frogs became a culinary island
treat.
>> Roasted frog.
>> I ate the legs and a little
bit of the ass, and now I'm
craving frog.
>> Did you eat the first one,
dude?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: And eating greens had
a whole new meaning.
>> Good morning, guys.
Got breakfast.
>> Oh, look at that.
>> PROBST: The survivors even
resorted to eating roots from
the water.
>> With some lime juice.
That would be good.
>> Courtney, do you want some of
this rice?
>> I do.
>> Did you guys just have this
like, today, really?
>> Is it okay?
>> PROBST: But nothing killed
appetites more than spoiled
rice.
>> Oh, my gosh.
This is so nasty.
>> The mother lode!
>> PROBST: And even clams were
questionable...
>> I don't think these things
are cooked all the way.
>> What?
>> All right, you eat it, then.
>> You think I'm not going to
eat that?
>> PROBST: ...which caused a lot
of bickering.
>> Just like with the damn rice.
I said the rice is bad, don't
eat it.
>> You did not say the rice is
bad.
Shut up, dude.
If somebody said the rice was
bad, I wouldn't have eaten it.
>> The survivors searched
everywhere...
>> Yes, dig for dinner.
>> PROBST: ...for anything
remotely edible.
>> Have y'all eaten one of these
things?
>> It's like, "Hey, he'll try
it."
>> After eating frog, I guess
I'll eat anything, huh?
>> PROBST: At the first immunity
challenge, lack of food and
sleep didn't fare well for Zhan
Hu.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: And Fei Long
prevailed.
Fei Long wins immunity!
That night, at tribal council,
Zhan Hu decided who was their
weakest link.
First person voted out of
Survivor: China, Chicken.
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: The next day at Fei
Long, Todd and Amanda formed an
alliance.
>> You're my long alliance, too.
>> Okay.
>> You have to have one in this
game.
You have to.
>> PROBST: And Aaron asserted
himself as the leader, calling
out Jean-Robert.
>> Jean-Robert, you need to
start pulling your weight.
>> I know that I'm not working
as much as I'd like to be able
to work.
My brain's working, but my
body's just not able to move
with it.
I wanted to give the perception
that I was a little bit lazy, so
later on when I am contributing
and putting in the work effort,
you know, people are noticing.
>> PROBST: But after a short
time, Aaron's actions caused
people to question his
leadership abilities.
>> I thought you were supposed
to be doing something.
I thought y'all were supposed to
be doing something.
We need to do the roof and get
some fire.
>> Yeah.
We tried and I couldn't do it.
>> So y'all going to stop?
Dude!
You're killing me.
>> Can you get fire?
Can you get fire?
>> You can.
We probably can together.
You're supposed to be the damn
leader.
Y'all are killing me.
The only reason why stuff gets
done is I don't want to sleep
on... get rained on.
I can't do all this stuff by
myself.
No, I'm not.
We're the only two to actually
do physical activity.
We've got a stewardess, we've
got two older ladies that don't
do much.
We've got a boy... he's a card
player, dude.
He came out here in Louis
Vittons.
>> James comes marching down
and, "Aaron, you're supposed to
be a leader.
You're supposed to be showing us
what to do, and you're down here
taking a nap."
And I'm, like, thinking he's
yelling at me at first.
I looked over at him, and he's
like, "You're just a flight
attendant.
I'm talking about him, our
leader."
And I was like, "Okay, let him
get ripped up," you know?
>> You have to help.
You have to help me out.
The rest of them, hey... you
need to get your ass up.
Come on.
There's just too much delegating
and a whole lot of nothing
getting done.
Now, I'm not going to do this by
myself anymore.
They're going to pull the rope
with me or they're all going to
die.
I'll move in that cave.
>> PROBST: Up next, Todd calls
out Jean-Robert.
>> Do you have a problem with
me, John-Robert?
>> Absolutely not.
>> That's not what I've heard.
>> Todd.
>> What?
>> First of all, fix your tone.
>> No.
>> Fix your tone.
>> PROBST: At the next reward
challenge...
Go!
...Fei Long rolled to their
second straight victory...
Fei Long wins!
...and a major element of the
game was revealed.
Fei Long, because you defeated
Zhan Hu, you now get to kidnap
one member of their tribe.
That person will come and live
with you until the next immunity
challenge.
Who are you going to kidnap?
>> Jaime.
>> PROBST: There's one more
layer to this twist.
Jaime, this is for you.
It says, "Open in private."
When you get to their beach,
find a private spot and read it.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: And if losing wasn't
bad enough, Zhan Hu was hit even
harder when they returned to
camp.
>> It looks like a natural
disaster hit our camp.
This is basically destroyed.
>> It was like somebody just
took all the water from every
ocean they could find and just
poured it right on top of us.
>> PROBST: And they quickly
devised a plan to restore their
camp.
>> I'm going in, I'm getting the
machete and I'm cutting a
channel.
>> Yeah, it was pretty
disheartening.
My first reaction was just, "Oh,
brother.
Here we go, something else to
worry about."
But, you know, when there's a
problem, you can only spend so
much time being worried about
it.
You really have to just, "All
right, let's fix it."
>> If you can at least cut
through some of those fibers and
those roots.
>> Oh, there you go, there you
go!
There it is.
>> Are they coming yet?
>> Yeah, it's starting.
>> Great effort.
We're digging channels, trying
to get our different plateaus to
drain.
We have three plateaus here at
our camp, and the top one's
draining into our living one,
which is draining into our
bamboo prep fields, which is
then tumbling two meters down
into the lake.
>> Hopefully, we'll be able to
get this really dry and finally
have a comfortable camp that's
not wet and muddy, so...
The water is actually starting
to flow now, so I think it's
actually working.
>> PROBST: That same day at Fei
Long, Jaime found a quiet place
to open the bamboo tube.
>> "In this sealed tube is a
clue to a hidden immunity idol
at the enemy camp.
You must give the sealed clue to
a member of the tribe."
My strategy, as far as the clue
goes, is I'm going to give it to
whom I think it is their weakest
link.
>> PROBST: In an attempt to be
strategic, Jaime gave the clue
to Leslie.
Don't let anybody know you have
it.
>> Okay.
I feel like the Lord really gave
me a gift.
>> PROBST: Leslie formed an
alliance of her own, hoping it
would help keep her in the game.
>> I told Todd the idol is here,
so we're going to team up and
use it together.
And I trust him.
>> I can't believe she told me.
I'm in shock!
I would never tell anybody.
What was she thinking?
>> PROBST: The next morning,
Aaron woke everyone up and
delivered some surprising news.
>> All right, so, making an
announcement.
It's been real, and it's been
fun, but it hasn't been real
fun.
>> I just can't stand all the
Brady Bunch antics that go on
in this tribe.
Aaron stood up this morning, put
on his little suit and jacket
with his little powwow.
Like, some of us haven't even
taken our heads off the bamboo
yet.
>> I am now relinquishing my
title as leader.
I can't continue to, like, keep
tabs on everyone else, and I
don't want to keep tabs on
everyone else.
But I've definitely enjoyed, you
know, helping out, you know,
with whatever advice I can give,
but I'm tired of making
decisions.
>> Aaron came up with this new
brilliant idea-- "I'm
relinquishing my leadership
position."
What?
>> All right, let's get some
fire.
so Amanda is on stairs.
Jean-Robert, you're going to do
logs with James later in the
day.
So does anyone know how to fish?
>> "No, I'm not the leader," and
right afterwards, he told us all
what to do.
>> PROBST: Over at Zhan Hu,
Dave's lack of sleep was
starting to affect him.
>> I'm up first primarily
because I got shuffled and
squeezed out of every
comfortable sleeping position
there is.
And if no one can see I'm the
tallest person around here,
that's starting to get under my
skin a little bit.
Hello.
You know?
>> PROBST: And Dave expressed
his views about eating before a
challenge.
>> We decided to do rice and
just a little bit so it will
boil faster.
We don't know how much time we
have to go before our challenge.
>> I'll tell you, man, eating
the rice right before a
challenge, I don't know.
I know that digestion diverts
all your energy to your stomach.
>> But we're all starving.
>> I'm... I'm... watch this.
Please, patience.
>> You're so dramatic.
>> Well, you know, I mentioned
this so many times.
And I have reasons for it.
>> I think it's better to eat
when you're starving before you
have to exert energy.
>> My physiology, my metabolism
is not yours.
Whatever you guys need to feel
better about it, if you feel
better after a meal, then by all
means, cook the rice.
>> If you don't want to eat,
that's...
Well, I don't think any of us
need to eat right now.
I just think it's smart to.
>> You guys know your bodies.
You guys start yourselves up.
I am not going to tell you what
to do, what not to do in that
respect.
>> Dave hasn't been eating.
He hasn't wanted to because he
says his energy is high.
He keeps telling everybody that
he somehow gets magical energy
from the air and he doesn't need
to eat.
I think he'd be smarter than
that.
>> Good things come to those who
wait.
I don't like doing things half-
assed.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Dave ate his words,
causing Zhan Hu to lose.
Fei Long wins immunity!
When Zhan Hu returned to camp,
Dave knew he was in the hot
seat.
>> I apologize.
I feel like I let us down today.
>> Start the fire.
>> Let me finish.
>> In the fireplace.
>> PROBST: And his constant
bickering with Ashley...
>> You're the leader, and I'm
going to let you do what you
want.
>> How many fires have you
built, sweetheart?
>> PROBST: ...put them both in
jeopardy.
At tribal council, Ashley ended
up getting the boot.
Ashley, the tribe has spoken.
The next morning at Fei Long,
Leslie cleaned up around camp.
>> Oh, they were?
Okay.
>> This morning, I woke up, and
I caught Leslie throwing away
our bait.
We caught it yesterday.
We needed that today to catch
the crabs and the fish.
And she thought there were too
many flies on it, so she threw
all our food away.
I was in shock.
I cannot believe how silly some
people can be.
>> Huh?
Huh?
Yeah.
>> And I'm really sorry, I threw
out those fish.
I didn't realize we were going
to use them for bait.
>> And tried to find them, and I
couldn't.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I know.
I have a learning curve.
You can yell at me.
You can scream at me.
I'm going to go down and try to
catch some more with the little
net, okay?
>> Uh-huh.
She wakes me up this morning and
tells me, "Oh, yeah, you need to
go fishing.
I'm like, "Cool, whatever."
"Oh, but I threw out the bait."
I don't understand that!
I mean, that's amazing.
I really would love to see how
these people would be without me
being here.
It would be hilarious, because
they honestly would be dead.
They'd be in the little boat
swimming, and would die of
thirst and hunger and just die
and float off in the river.
>> PROBST: At the next immunity
challenge....
>> Get that off my finger!
>> PROBST: Todd struggled with
the puzzle.
>> Move it from my face!
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu wins
immunity!
With Fei Long facing their first
tribal council, Jean-Robert
started placing blame on others.
>> What's on your mind regarding
today's challenge?
>> It's a strategy thing and we
messed it up.
It's that simple.
>> You know, you guys said we're
all promoting Todd to put the
things in, so I didn't want to
get in his way, but I handed
them all in the right places.
It was a matter of going up or
down.
You know, it wasn't that
complicated a puzzle.
>> Did you... did you realize
this and then...
>> I let Todd take the charge
and he was doing it, and it
looked like he was doing just
fine for a while.
>> Now Jean-Robert is spinning
it that Todd didn't do the
puzzle right, so it's always
someone else besides him.
But, like, I don't care.
I'll vote for snoreface
Jean-Robert because he annoys
the crap out of me.
>> Okay, I'm going to leave you
guys.
I just wanted to...
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: And Todd became very
defensive.
>> You have a problem with me,
Jean-Robert, thinking I screwed
up the puzzle or something?
>> Absolutely not.
>> That's not what I've heard.
>> So what did you hear?
>> Someone said that you thought
that I screwed up the puzzle.
>> I didn't say any such thing.
>> You've got to watch your
mouth, dude.
Word gets around.
>> Todd, first of all, fix your
tone.
>> No.
>> Fix your tone.
>> Who said I said... James,
were you here?
Did I say he screwed up the
puzzle?
I'm asking you, James.
You were here.
Did I say he screwed up the
puzzle?
Amanda, did I say that Todd
screwed up the puzzle?
>> Amanda wasn't here.
She was with me, dude.
>> Aaron, did I say that Todd
screwed up the puzzle?
>> No.
>> Thank you.
So when you come confronting me,
make sure you know what you're
talking about.
>> That's why I came straight to
you, Jean-Robert.
>> Okay, but you came to me with
a tone.
>> Okay, well, wouldn't you?
>> Listen, we're all upset
because we lost a challenge.
>> Okay.
>> So all I'm saying is what
could we have done better?
You, absolutely, were not even
close to being one of the people
accountable for messing up
today.
>> All right, sorry for freaking
on you.
I just want to clear it out.
>> All right.
>> I get a little crazy like
that, okay?
>> Yeah, all right.
>> So, of course, I run back to
camp and kind of lose it on
Jean-Robert for a second, and I
wanted to put him in his place
and let him realize, "Yeah, you
know, I'm 150 pounds lighter
than you, dude, but I have a
very, very strong opinion, and
I'm going to knock you down if I
have to."
>> This team hates to lose.
>> Everybody gets kind of on
edge.
>> This team hates to lose.
That's one good thing.
>> PROBST: But at tribal
council, Fei Long kept Jean-
Robert for his strength.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: China...
And Leslie was voted out.
Up next:
>> If we lose, you're going
home.
That's not my call.
>> PROBST: Frosti gets handed an
ultimatum.
>> It's either we win and end up
going really far in the game or
lose and go home.
>> PROBST: By the morning of day
ten, Courtney had reached her
boiling point with Jean-Robert.
>> Don't touch that!
Don't touch that!
>> Okay, sorry.
I was afraid it might be hot.
>> He's, like, a cocky son of a
bitch, and he sucks so bad.
There's no getting out of that.
>> PROBST: Later that day at the
immunity challenge...
Sherea launches again!
...Sherea gave a brave
performance.
And scores!
But her efforts were not
enough...
James connects again.
...as Fei Long won another
challenge.
( cheers )
After another loss, Sherea and
Dave were at each other's
throats.
>> Sherea, please do not throw
those away.
>> I wish you would touch me.
I wish... I wish you would touch
me.
>> I'm saving some of these
shells.
>> Back up off me.
>> I'm saving...
>> Back up off of me.
>> Would you please...
>> If it were up to me, if we
could get rid of both of them,
it would be great.
>> Do not walk up on me again.
>> PROBST: And at tribal
council, Zhan Hu decided they'd
had enough of Dave.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: China, Dave.
>> Someone's coming in.
>> PROBST: On day 13, another
twist was revealed.
>> Ah!
>> Fei Long, choose the two
warriors from Zhan Hu who you
feel could best help to
strengthen your tribe.
>> PROBST: The tribes were mixed
up.
Sherea and Frosti had to move to
the Fei Long tribe.
>> Hey, guys.
>> PROBST: And James and Aaron
had to move to the Zhan Hu
tribe.
>> What's going on, guys?
>> Hello.
>> PROBST: With the new tribes
in place, Fei Long took some
time to lighten things up around
camp.
>> I... I...
( laughter )
>> But I don't... I don't know.
>> I would have to say that...
that... that... that... winning
is... god, it's so good!
>> That was great.
( applause )
( laughter )
>> I don't even know how it
started, but we started doing
impressions.
And we did Jean-Robert, and how
he just likes to talk about
himself, and Todd stuck out his
belly, how Jean-Robert does.
And I was like, "Keep going,
don't stop."
This is what me and my friends
do at home.
We sit around and we jaw on each
other.
That means talk about each
>> You guys...
>> You guys, if we just work
together...
>> I'm kind of like liking you.
You're like, "Over on the other
side over there, we wasn't
eatin' anything.
There was... okay."
( laughter )
>> Oh, I know he ain't going
to...
>> You put your one hand, and
you shake your ass.
>> People do say I walk like
that.
>> Denise-- "Oh, I don't care.
Everybody get in the car.
We go down to Salem, we get
ourselves some Bud.
I do some karate.
I just don't care.
At all, about anything."
>> Oh, my God.
>> Jeff...
( laughter )
"We're team Abercrombie and
Fitch, and you guys are all,
like, team you know, what's
left."
And then sometimes it's the one
eye, like, real open.
"Okay."
And the butt goes out more and
more.
It's the visible thinking.
That's what gets me.
It's, like, the visible thought
process.
And she's like... like when they
finish the challenges, she's
like... it gets, like, more
intense.
She's like, "I'm ready to go."
( laughter )
"I'm ready."
"Yo, when I compete, it's on."
With her little boobies and her
hot pink bikini, and she
bartends at a frat house.
And it's like, "Can I order you
online?
Like, aren't there ads for you
in the back of a magazine
somewhere?"
Like, come on.
>> PROBST: But over at Zhan Hu,
things were all business with
Jaime and Peih-Gee.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
>> Boys, take your time and just
get your breath first.
Wait a minute.
Wait a long minute.
>> PROBST: Jaime and Peih-Gee's
plan was set in motion.
Fei Long wins immunity!
And Aaron was the fifth person
voted out of Survivor: China.
The next day at the reward
challenge...
Fei Long wins reward.
James was kidnapped by his old
tribe.
James, this is for you.
Once back at Fei Long, James put
his fate in Todd's hands.
>> I know what they're talking
about.
It's those stupid bats above the
freaking thing.
>> PROBST: Todd and Amanda found
the hidden immunity idol, but
Frosti unexpectedly got
involved.
>> Hey, hey, hey, hey!
All I could think was "Frosti,
Frosti, no."
So Todd and Amanda came up with
a new plan for James to take the
immunity idol and throw the next
challenge in order to save
himself.
>> If you're running, trip.
James loses immunity.
They vote for him, but he uses
the idol to get rid of Jaime.
>> PROBST: Then Todd told James
about the second hidden immunity
idol at the Zhan Hu camp.
>> All I have to do is stay
focused, get the other idol and
then I'll have both of them.
I mean, it's going to be
wonderful.
I'm having a great time.
>> PROBST: But with Frosti now
in the mix, Todd and Amanda had
to make a foolproof plan.
>> People have said if we lose,
you're going home.
That's not my call.
So, I mean, it will... it will
help, though, for you to fight
even harder to win, because it's
either win and end up going
really far in the game, or lose
and go home.
Do you know what I mean?
And I like you way too much to
send you home.
>> We're not trying to blackmail
you.
>> I promise I'm not.
I promise I'm not trying to play
godfather.
I like you way too much to watch
you go 11th place, dude.
Way too much.
If we lose today, Frosti knows
he's going home, because he saw
the hidden immunity idol, and he
knows our plan now, so we had to
throw that blackmail in his face
and say "Look, this is how it
is.
You have an ultimatum-- win and
stay, lose, go home."
>> How do you feel right now?
>> Yeah, you look kind of
dumbstruck.
>> Well, I mean, you know I have
to be on your side.
>> Yeah.
I trust you now, because...
( laughter )
>> That makes me sound horrible.
>> We blackmailed Frosti because
we don't want him giving any
information to Zhan Hu today,
and with Frosti helping us win
as much as he can, and James
helping Zhan Hu lose as much as
he can, I'm pretty confident
that we'll win the challenge
today.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Go.
...Frosti put his best foot
forward in an effort to stay in
the game.
Frosti, he's licking the plate.
Fei Long scores!
These are chicken fetuses.
Go.
James spitting it back up.
Denise is struggling.
But Denise couldn't get her head
around the task...
>> Sorry, James.
>> PROBST: ...ruining James'
and Todd's perfect plan.
>> I got it.
>> Chew it!
>> That's right, baby.
>> PROBST: James puts it all in
his mouth.
James scores for Zhan Hu.
>> Genius idea.
Smashed.
>> PROBST: That night at tribal
council, Frosti's ongoing
loyalty paid off.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: China.
And Sherea was voted out.
Even though James and Todd's
plan didn't pan out, James'
spirits were up when he found
the second hidden immunity idol.
>> That's funny.
I'm on Survivor with two idols.
>> PROBST: Later that day, Jaime
and Erik found a discarded
plaque that James had left
behind.
>> This used to be hanging on
the archway.
And it looks like someone took
it off.
>> It could definitely say,
like, immunity idol in Chinese
and I'd have no idea.
It's a weird symbol, so I don't
know what it stands for.
>> PROBST: James had to laugh
when he noticed the plaque was
gone.
>> The thought of this woman
having a blank one...
that would be the best ever, if
she pulls out a blank thing and
everyone's like, "What do you
mean?
It don't have the writing on
there.
You at least have to have
something.
One of these!"
>> PROBST: That night when James
was away from camp, Jaime
decided to do some snooping.
But in the dark, she was unable
to differentiate James's idols
from her own.
On day 20...
Drop your buffs.
...the tribes merged.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: ...and had a
celebratory feast.
>> Oh, my God!
We get to eat!
>> Yeah, girls!
>> PROBST: And the party carried
on throughout the night.
>> Who is over there?
Is that Erik and Jaime?
Jamie, is that you?
>> I'm not drunk, I'm not drunk.
>> Jaime, is that you?
>> No, this is Erik.
>> Is that Erik?
Erik, hey, what's up?
>> Hey!
>> You guys, I think we're on
the last legs of this canteen.
It's almost drained.
Todd is definitely... Todd is
done.
>> I'm closing out Todd.
I'm closing out Amanda.
Courtney....
>> You guys, this is not good.
>> Tonight at the feast, we had
some, like, potent snake sake.
I don't know what was in it, but
it was really strong.
You could feel it in burning in
your mouth a few seconds after.
>> This is like Survivor: the
Musical.
>>  We live in the jungle
in a tree house
With a leaking roof
They have no tarp
even though they won it
but we have fire...
>>  I haven't had snake wine
because I don't drink.
>> They sing when they're sober.
They'll sing all day and all
night.
It's like a little musical over
here.
I knew the alcohol would only
heighten it.
>> What?
>> Oh, my God!
>> The guys broke out the wine,
and they've been sucking it down
the last couple hours and a
couple of them are pretty tipsy
right now.
I'm a little older than the rest
of the kids.
I don't want to be having a
hangover.
But I think definitely Todd and
definitely Amanda aren't going
to be feeling too well in the
morning.
>> PROBST: On day 21, Jaime felt
secure with her place in the
game.
>> If Todd sees me play the
hidden immunity idol tonight,
he's definitely going to be
floored.
I think it's probably going to
shock everyone, including Jeff.
I'm not as dumb as I look, and
maybe they're figuring it out.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Jaime played what she thought
was an immunity idol.
>> I found this at camp lying on
the floor.
So I thought it might be
immunity.
>> PROBST: This is not a hidden
immunity idol.
But her hopes were tossed aside.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: China, and the first
member of our jury, Jaime.
Jaime, the tribe has spoken.
And Jaime became the first
member of the jury.
Up next, Peih-Gee tries to make
amends.
>> You can accept it or not.
>> No.
>> But I really am sorry.
>> You're really not.
Please, stop messing with me and
go sit down somewhere else.
>> PROBST: On the morning of day
23, James took some time alone
to clear his thoughts.
>> They're a bunch of late
sleepers over here.
They're just so tired.
You've got to motivate yourself.
I'm a grave digger.
I've been doing it my whole
life.
My dad handed me a shovel
at 11 and told me to start
working.
And that's all I've ever done.
All I do is work.
I'm used to being in the hot sun
with a shovel in my hand.
And over here, there's nothing
for me to do but, you know,
provide.
I like cooking.
I like catching fish.
I love providing for people.
I mean, that's what I do.
It's one of the reasons I'm
still here.
I mean, granted, the two idols I
do have are a big part of it,
but I make life easy over here.
I am that guy who's been kind of
the glue of the alliance.
I feel like I am the one who is
holding everybody together.
It's just right there.
It's so simple.
All we have to do is stick
together, and we'll be there.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Courtney was the last
one sitting.
Courtney wins immunity!
Facing tribal council, Erik
filled Jean-Robert in on the
secret behind the immunity
idols.
>> We looked in James' bag and
there were two of them.
>> Wow.
This is the guy favored to win
every challenge from here out.
>> PROBST: So Jean-Robert
confronted James.
>> You have two immunity idols?
Two of them and you can't tell
your boy?
Nobody told me, bro.
...is the realization that
you're holding out on me.
That's what I came up with.
>> PROBST: Jean-Robert came up
with a plan to take out his
closest ally.
We could blindside him tonight,
because he will not pull out the
idol tonight.
>> Let's see how it goes
tonight.
I was kind of bothered by the
fact he's coming up with all
these ideas that I've had for
days now.
>> PROBST: But Todd turned the
tables on Jean-Robert.
>> I think our best bet is...
>> I don't want to break the
system, but...
>> Do we want to tell Denise or
no?
>> No-- hell no!
>> PROBST: But at tribal
council, James took the risk of
not using one of his idols...
James.
...and almost paid the price.
James received three votes.
One vote left.
But in the end, Jean-Robert with
five votes was dealt a losing
hand.
Jean-Robert, the tribe has
spoken.
At the reward challenge, Peih-
Gee was captain of the red team,
Erik captain of the yellow.
Go.
Peih-Gee's team dropped the
ball.
James, too hard, Peih-Gee can't
get it.
And Erik's team bounced to
victory.
Frosti, Amanda, Erik, and
Courtney, cruising down the
river.
>> All right, everyone, cheers
to us.
>> PROBST: During the cruise,
Courtney grew closer to Frosti.
>> I love my Frosti.
I love my Frosti.
>> PROBST: Back at camp,
Peih-Gee blamed James for losing
the challenge.
That's why y'all lose.
You're quick to blame.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I can finish?
Can I please finish?
>> No, you can't, because I
don't care.
>> You know, I need to take a
walk right now.
>> Peih-Gee, she's just stupid.
>> PROBST: After she cooled off,
Peih-Gee tried to make amends.
>> No, you're not.
Don't politic.
>> I'm not politicking.
I'm apologizing.
So you can accept it or you're
not, but I really am sorry,
okay?
>> No, you're not.
You're really not.
>> Please stop messing with me
and go sit down somewhere else.
>> No, I came up to apologize.
I didn't come out to fight with
you some more, okay?
>> Well, obviously, you did.
>> You know what?
Listen, that's cool.
You're not in the mood to accept
my apology, that's fine.
I can understand that.
>> I know what kind of person
You are, and this is just a
bunch of fluff, and I really
don't like fluff.
I'm not a fluff person.
>> James....
>> I'm really not.
>> After losing the reward
challenge, I was really pissed
to have lost, but I shouldn't
have taken it out on James.
So, I don't know.
I'm in, like, a really bad
position.
>> PROBST: But at the immunity
challenge...
Peih-Gee wins immunity.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: ...Peih-Gee narrowly
beats Frosti.
With Peih-Gee immune, the former
Fei Long saw Frosti as the
biggest threat.
>> He's got to go before Erik.
>> Has to go.
>> PROBST: And Todd tried to
sway Courtney's decision.
>> Frosti's kind of like my
little munchkin.
And everyone's kind of worried
about me because they know he's,
you know, like, my good friend.
>> PROBST: That night at tribal
council...
Ninth person voted out and the
third member of our jury...
...Todd's efforts paid off.
Frosti, the tribe has spoken.
All right.
Tonight, you will not be heading
directly back to camp.
We have more business to attend
to here.
>> PROBST: Where 16 once stood,
only seven remain.
How will James choose to use his
two immunity idols?
>> I have the big joker and the
little joker, so I'm going to be
here for a while, so you might
as well go on and get
comfortable.
>> PROBST: What new adventures
will the survivors face?
What future twist will the
challenges bring?
Today, you are playing for....
>> What?
>> PROBST: Join us as the
adventure continues.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: next time on
Survivor:
Tonight, you will not be heading
directly back to camp.
A twist at tribal council
catches everyone off guard.
We have more business to attend
to here.
And Amanda turns on her
alliance.
>> Fei Long is not together
anymore.
>> That is not a new style for
Denise.
I believe that the USA hockey
team is missing a player.
I mean, the flight attendant
voice is getting to me.
You can almost hear everyone
opening their little bag of
peanuts every time he says
something.
Peih-Gee seems kind of smug,
like, "Yum, I love me some pig
knuckles."
Any guy who shows up to the
middle of the jungle in a silk
shirt and no underpants, you've
got to wonder about that guy.