>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
Drop your buffs.
...after the two tribes
merged...
>> One big, happy family.
>> PROBST: ...James had the only
two hidden immunity idols.
>> James, he's almost guaranteed
himself in the top five right
now.
>> That's funny.
I'm on Survivor with two idols.
>> PROBST: And the members of
the former Zhan Hu Tribe were on
the chopping block.
>> The plan was to get rid of
Peih-Gee, then Erik and Frosti
after that.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge, there was a school-
yard pick where everyone was
chosen to compete except Denise.
>> We're going to go with
Courtney because she's light.
>> PROBST: You will not
participate in this challenge.
You'll not be eligible for the
reward.
Take a spot on the bench.
And back at camp, she was
feeling left out.
>> Are they going to do that
when it comes down to the final
seven?
Am I going to be the one that's
going to go home before JR?
And I going to be the one that
goes home before James?
I don't want to be that person.
>> PROBST: And Courtney's
allegiance to the Fei Long
alliance was also wavering.
>> You got to watch Courtney,
because she is a loose cannon.
She does stray off and fall in
love with anybody that floats
and smiles at her.
>> PROBST: So Peih-Gee jumped at
the small opening by trying to
lure Denise and Courtney into
her alliance.
>> There's five of us here.
If we all band together, it'll
be four to five; we can pick
them off one by one.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Courtney was the last
one sitting.
Courtney wins immunity!
Facing tribal council, Jean-
Robert discovered that James had
both idols.
>> This is the guy who's favored
to win every challenge from here
out.
>> PROBST: So he came up with a
plan to take out his closest
ally.
>> We could blindside him
tonight, because he will not
pull out the idol tonight.
>> PROBST: But Todd turned the
tables on Jean-Robert.
>> I think our best bet is Jean-
Robert.
>> Yeah, I don't want... I don't
like breaking the system.
>> You don't want to tell Denise
or no?
>> No, hell no.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
James took the risk of not using
his idol...
James.
...and almost paid the price.
He received three votes and
Peih-Gee received one.
One vote left.
But in the end, Jean-Robert was
dealt a losing hand.
Jean-Robert, the tribe has
spoken.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I had a narrow escape last
night.
I had three votes.
I mean, now all I have to do is
stay on my Ps and Qs.
But, you know, the odds of me
actually being kicked off with
the two idols are not that hot.
So from now on, I'll have them
with me on tribal council.
( clearing throat )
♪ Good morning
good morning!
♪ I come to say good morning
good morning
♪ Good morning to you! ♪
>> Good morning.
>> That was beautiful, by the
way.
>> Everyone, it's Christmas!
There's no Jean-Robert in the
bed!
Camp life without John-Robert is
much nicer, and I think that
everyone else is also kind of
happy to have him gone.
Jean-Robert is such a complainer
and demanding people to fetch
him things and just... just
generally unpleasant.
>> Denise was, like, shooting
daggers at myself and Amanda
because she was mad.
By blindsiding Jean-Robert, we
had to blindside her too, and it
could come back to get us.
>> We have a plan here that the
former Fei Long, we're going to
vote out the Zhan Hu people.
So last night at tribal council,
I went with the original plan.
I voted Peih-Gee, like we were
supposed to.
But I guess at the last moment,
everybody changed their minds,
and half the tribe voted for
Jean-Robert.
It kind of makes me feel on the
outside, because I had an
opportunity to switch over to
Zhan Hu, and I decided to stay
with the group that I'm close
to.
And I still get backstabbed.
It's a hard position for me
right now.
>> You okay?
The thing with last night, I
don't know what happened.
Everybody freaked out because...
>> But they were supposed to
tell you at the end.
>> I mean, I felt like an idiot.
I'm the only one that voted for
Peih-Gee.
At the last second, they should
have told me.
>> That's what the plan was,
honestly.
>> You know, I mean, how I do
feel at the end now?
Do I feel like I'm the next one
to go because I'm an idiot?
>> No, you're still safe.
Just don't... we need to hold
this together.
>> James has two hidden immunity
idols.
It's smart to stick with him.
I mean, you never know what's
going to happen, but it is hard
to trust people in this game.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> You want the fire died down a
little or...
>> No, I'm about to pick it back
up.
>> You want it really hot.
>> Yeah, thanks for telling me.
You're wanting to micromanaging
me.
>> I'm just excited, okay?
I'm just excited to eat.
>> Oh, my gosh, Jean-Robert was
annoying, and now he's gone, but
all of a sudden Peih-Gee decided
to step in and take his place.
>> I'm sorry.
I wasn't trying to micromanage
you.
>> Even though Peih-Gee's not
playing a very smart game, but
the thing is is Courtney, she's
tight with Frosti, and she's
flirting with him.
>> I know.
No hot dogs, but pretty close.
>> I mean, it's scary.
It really is.
Because you never know if she's
going to want to twist or turn,
and that kind of worries me.
>> Tree mail!
And we have a drum.
>> You guys ready?
>> Yes.
>> "An experience of a lifetime
in a truly magical place, a
feast of sights to feed your
soul, and you'll also feed your
face.
Again you must divide to
conquer.
You better be on the ball.
If you drum up some enthusiasm,
you might just win it all."
>> That drum is wicked.
>> I just want to win.
I just hate that, like, I'm the
most losingest survivor left in
this game right now.
Like, I've lost the most
challenges out of everybody.
Like, it kind of sucks, and that
makes me want to win even more.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
reward challenge.
>> Yes.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will be divided
into two teams of four.
Using four different-sized
drums, you must keep a ball in
the air by bouncing it from one
drum to another as you navigate
through a series of obstacles.
Along the way, you'll pass
through two gates.
If you drop the ball, you've got
to return to the start or the
previous gate.
When you reach the end, you must
bounce the ball in a finish bin,
then race back to the start.
First team to get three balls in
their bin wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: The winning team of
four will be treated to a
spectacular cruise on the Lee
River.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: One of the most
beautiful spots in China.
You'll have a nice dinner, spend
the night on the boat, return to
camp in the morning.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: We're going to
randomly choose captains.
This is a school-yard pick.
Peih-Gee, you're the captain of
the red team.
Erik, you're the captain of the
yellow team.
You will rock, paper, scissor to
see who picks first.
>> One, two, three.
>> PROBST: Scissor cuts paper.
Peih-Gee, you get the first
choice.
>> James.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee doesn't even
hesitate.
Peih-Gee selects James.
>> PROBST: Erik, your choice.
>> Frosti.
>> PROBST: Erik selects Frosti.
James, your choice.
>> Todd.
>> PROBST: Todd joins James and
Peih-Gee.
Frosti, who you want?
>> I think we'll go with Amanda.
>> PROBST: Amanda coming over to
join Erik and Frosti.
>> PROBST: Todd you have the
last choice between Courtney and
Denise.
>> Denise.
>> PROBST: Todd takes Denise.
Courtney will join Erik, Frosti,
and Amanda.
We have our two teams.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize.
We'll get started.
For a cruise down the Lee River,
a nice meal, and a good night's
sleep.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Both groups off to a good,
smooth start.
Todd and Erik taking it all the
way up to the first obstacle.
Going to have to pass sooner or
later.
Erik passes to Frosti.
Red team loses it.
You got to go back to the start.
Yellow group's made it through
the first gate.
If you drop the ball, that will
be your starting point.
Frosti almost losing it.
Off his head, he does.
Back to this mat here.
There is definitely a learning
curve to this challenge.
James loses it.
Red heads back to the start
again.
Nice pass, Erik keeping it
alive.
They're through the second gate.
>> Okay, guys, don't panic.
Here we go.
>> PROBST: Yellow getting very
close.
>> Erik.
>> PROBST: Frosti back to Erik.
Now they just got to get it in
the finish bin.
And they do!
Nice teem teamwork.
Yellow scores one!
You need three to win.
Denise, Peih-Gee, Todd, James,
having a tough time getting the
hang of this.
Whereas Courtney, Erik, Frosti,
and Amanda having much more
success.
>> Let me know of any obstacles.
>> Just watch out for the mud,
obstacle.
>> PROBST: Both teams at the
first obstacle.
It's about teamwork.
Todd goes to Peih-Gee.
Peih-Gee keeps it alive.
>> You got it, Todd.
>> PROBST: Red doing a good job.
Both teams go through the first
gate.
Frosti passes back to Erik.
>> Toss it to me.
>> PROBST: Todd goes to Peih-
Gee.
Peih-Gee keeps it alive.
>> Todd, you ready?
Take over.
>> PROBST: Red misses again.
Frosti to Erik, a nice save by
Erik.
Another nice save by Erik.
Yellow again very close.
Yellow very close to scoring
their second point.
Yellow leads two-zip!
Red team got to make this one
count.
Peih-Gee keeping it alive.
Todd with a nice save.
>> Get over the line.
Get over the thing.
>> PROBST: Red trying to score
their first point.
Todd to Peih-Gee, red very
close.
But they lose it.
>> Grab the ball!
Get back!
Come on!
>> PROBST: Erik leading yellow
up the hill with that third and
final ball.
Red team still on their first,
starting to panic.
James, too hard, Peih-Gee can't
get it.
Yellow's making good ground with
that third and final ball.
They've got a good rhythm going.
>> Get it!
Get it!
>> PROBST: Red close, but misses
again.
Red has to go back to the mat.
As yellow heads up the hill with
that third and final ball, they
seem to have figured this out.
Erik to Frosti.
This could be it.
Big reward on the line if they
get it in.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: And they do!
Frosti, Amanda, Erik, and
Courtney cruising down the Lee
River.
Okay, Erik, Frosti, Courtney,
Amanda, you will leave from
here, be taken to the Lee River.
You will return to camp in the
morning.
James, Peih-Gee, Denise, Todd,
your looks say it all.
I got nothing for you.
Get your stuff.
Head back to camp.
The reward is waiting.
Head out and have a good time.
>> Thank you.
>> Uh-uh.
I did not see your ass strolling
back to the mat every time we
dropped the ball.
>> Uh-huh.
I'm the one who was dropping the
ball today?
>> No, I was the only one.
>> I'm not saying it's your
fault, James.
I'm not saying... no... what I'm
saying is... I want...
Can I finish?
Can I please finish?
>> No, you can't, because I
don't care.
Please stop messing with me.
Because every time you bring
something up, I will quickly
blast you back and make you look
quite silly.
>> Yeah?
>> Because every time you open
your mouth, you're just speaking
nonsense.
That's why you lose.
>> Really?
My ass wasn't strolling back to
the mat after ever time.
I raced back to that damn mat.
You know, I need to take a walk
right now.
>> Peih-Gee, she's just stupid.
I mean, she really came to me
and said that I was the reason
why they didn't... it's all my
fault.
Maybe she's the problem.
She's never won anything.
I mean, maybe that's the sign.
You know, not everybody is
crazy.
You're the crazy one.
>> I'm probably pissed off that
we lost the challenge, and I'm
taking it out on James, but I'm
the only person who wasn't won
any reward challenges.
I'm pissed about it.
Like, I'd love to go on a
reward, but I don't have a
single ally here.
I don't have anybody.
I'm in, like, a really bad
position.
It's probably not smart to go
around picking fights with
people, but I can't, like, keep
my mouth shut sometimes.
>> Oh, I didn't hear what she
was saying, but I heard her
yelling.
>> She came over to me, saying
it's my fault we lost.
>> It's your fault?
>> Yeah, my fault, because I let
the ball drop...
>> She dropped the ball a couple
times.
Everybody did.
>> Everybody dropped the ball.
It just wasn't our day.
But that thing... she... ooh.
Is she serious?
>> I don't like her attitude at
all.
>> She really came over here and
was blaming me.
That's some nerve.
>> It is nerve.
It's crazy.
>> That's why we need to focus.
We need to keep trying to focus,
and we all need to focus and
just pick them people off.
I'm trying to keep away from
temptation from Zhan Hu.
Them little pretty boys and the
little annoying little girl,
they are still enemies.
They're still trying to
infiltrate the force to get
where we already have
predestined ourselves to be.
Amanda is going to be all right.
Courtney, she's flaky, but she's
going to fall in line.
Her... hopefully her and what's
his name don't have a big
romance tonight, which might
happen.
That would hurt.
It makes no sense for us to mess
it up now, but it's so human
nature.
I mean, it's right there in
front of you.
Just don't eat the damn apple.
Be naked and be happy.
Don't eat that damn apple.
I hope that Courtney don't flip.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Because Courtney would do
that for love.
>> This is probably the worst
day that I can have out here.
People are freaking out around
camp, and the four people I get
along best with are out having a
good time on a boat somewhere.
Today sucks.
>> All right, everyone, cheers
to us.
Cheers!
>> Cheers.
>> What great win today.
>> Yeah.
>> What a good win.
I haven't won hardly any
challenges since I've been out
here, so I was amped up to win.
The reward was for this cruise
on the Lee River.
It was spectacular.
I felt like it was a pretty cool
group of people, and you know,
of course it was a good
opportunity to just get to know
them a little better and try
and, you know, develop
relationships.
I'm just wondering what it's
like back at camp.
>> I like Peih-Gee.
I just...
>> I wanted to like her.
>> She's making me annoyed with
her.
>> She is cool, like, when she's
relaxing and just kind of
hanging.
>> Yeah, but she's...
>> She's totally cool.
>> She's too intense right now,
and I don't... I don't like
that.
>> She doesn't want to lose, and
I think she feels like she's
powerless, but, like, she's made
a series of poor decisions.
>> As much as I'm, like, still
basically on Peih-Gee's side, I
don't mind her being talked
about negatively simply because
it means if she's getting talked
about, then I'm not.
>> Here's to us.
>> Yeah.
>> Because we're still here.
>> Whoo!
>> Yay!
>> And on a boat.
>> This is definitely where I
want to be.
>> And the night is young.
>> The night is young.
>> And I'm feeling quite jolly
already.
>> Yay!
Jolly!
I love my Frosti.
I don't really understand my
relationship with Frosti.
He's young.
He's only 20.
And he's kind of cute.
He just wants to play.
I love our reward.
The path of righteousness has
led us in the right direction.
>> I like Courtney a lot.
And I think both of us feel
that, and that's good.
She's a really attractive girl.
She's smart.
She's way out of my league, but
having somebody that you're just
comfortable around is really
nice.
>> Look how high that is
straight up.
>> Oh, my God, unreal.
This is like the greatest
adventure, like, in China
possible.
Oh, my gosh, it's a goat, you
guys!
I'm not even kidding.
>> Where?
>> That black thing right there.
>> And the white thing.
( Erik imitating a goat )
>> That's good.
Not only does it sound good.
You do the face.
( Erik imitating a goat )
Erik, stop hitting on the goats.
They're a couple.
( Erik imitating a goat )
>> I feel like we had a great
time together.
Maybe it helped me in Courtney
and Amanda's eyes, and maybe
that's enough to at least save
me another round.
( Erik imitating a goat )
>> I think that's the greatest
impression I've ever heard.
Congratulations, Erik.
>> I do what I can.
I do what I can.
>> I really like Erik.
I know he's here to play the
game as well, but I think he's
adorable, and I definitely want
to see him around as long as
possible.
I really like him.
>> Oh, my God!
Is that fried chicken?
Oh, my god!
This is the greatest day of my
life.
What is that?
Mashed potatoes.
Thank you!
>> Thank you!
>> Oh, my God.
>> Fried chicken!
>> Erik, he is a threat, and
he's been doing a really good
job of getting close to Amanda
and Courtney.
I don't know, it does worry me,
just because... I mean, there's
no reason they couldn't be like,
"Oh, well, why don't we just
take Erik instead of Frosti?"
It's scary.
I don't want to be replaced.
>> Someone's coming in.
Hey, bitches, welcome home!
>> Hey.
>> We want to hear all about it.
>> Juicy details.
>> We had Chinese food, the same
thing that we had...
>> Chinese food.
>> Oh, it was so fun.
Talk it up.
We need details.
>> We lied to everyone because
if we would have told them we
would have had fried chicken,
mashed potatoes, and bread and
butter, everyone would have
hated us for sure.
>> It was a nice cruise though.
>> No, it was really cool.
>> It was nice, and the scenery
was beautiful.
>> It was really pretty.
>> It was nice.
>> What's been going on around
here, just the same old, trying
to get food and water?
>> Pretty much.
>> Todd, we missed you.
>> It's so nice to have you guys
back, though.
I mean, this is the thing.
Like, you know, believe it or
not, Peih-Gee just lost it and
just started screaming at James.
>> When you guys got back?
>> Yeah.
Screaming at James, like, "You
can't bounce a ball on a drum
and..." da, da, da, da.
She freaked out on him.
>> Oh, my God.
>> He was like, "Bitch, what are
you talking about?"
>> That sounds like a Jean-
Robert move.
>> Yeah, it is a Jean-Robert
move.
>> Peih-Gee is not necessarily
in most people's good graces
right now, so hopefully I'll be
safe, unless Peih-Gee wins
immunity, and then it's a whole
new story.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First thing's first.
Courtney, time to give it up.
>> Oh, and it looked so cute on
her too.
>> PROBST: Once again immunity
is back up for grabs.
Today's immunity challenge will
test your memory.
You will each have a series of
Chinese zodiac symbols in front
of you.
Each round, I will call out a
list of those symbols.
You must then use your knife to
stab them in the correct order.
Get it right, you stay in.
Get it wrong, you're out.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, is guaranteed a one-
in-seven shot at winning this
game.
Losers, tribal council tonight,
somebody will be going home.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: If you feel so
comfortable you don't think you
need immunity tonight, you can
opt not to play in the challenge
and instead...
>> No.
>> PROBST: ...you can eat.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh!
>> That's okay.
>> Don't do that.
>> That is so wrong.
>> PROBST: Cheeseburgers.
French fries.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Cold drinks.
>> PROBST: And all the fixings.
>> Oh, my God!
>> That is mean!
>> PROBST: I'm going to give
each of you a white coin and a
black coin.
Black means you want to eat.
White means you want to play.
I'll hand them out.
Don't do anything with them yet.
Keep them both together.
Make sure they're separated.
Black means you want to eat.
White means you want to play.
This is a simple case of
temptation.
So now I want everybody to
choose one coin, put it in your
right hand, put your right hand
out.
Three, two, one, reveal.
Courtney's decided she wants to
eat.
Todd is going to eat.
Denise is going to eat.
And James is going to eat.
Take a spot at your feast bench.
Peih-Gee, Frosti, Amanda, and
Erik are playing to win this
game.
All right, here's how it will
work.
When we start, you guys can
begin eating.
You can eat for as long as the
challenge takes, until we have a
winner.
The challenge is now beginning.
Dig in.
Here we go, first round.
Tiger, rabbit, rat, monkey, dog.
Go.
Let's see how we do.
Tiger, rat is wrong.
Erik, take a spot.
Tiger, rabbit, rat, monkey, dog
is right.
Amanda is still in.
Tiger, rabbit, rat, monkey, dog
is right.
Peih-Gee is still in.
Tiger, rabbit, rat, monkey, dog.
Frosti is still in.
Erik, that has got to be tough
now.
You didn't make it one round,
and you're looking at
cheeseburgers, fries, fixings.
>> Can't do anything about it.
I'm going to make the most of
it, sit here, and smell it.
>> PROBST: Courtney, how's that
burger?
>> Great.
>> Probably the best food I've
ever had in my life right now.
>> PROBST: We are down to three.
Next round: rat, ram, dragon,
rooster, ram.
Frosti struggling to get that
last one.
You're committed to what you
have.
>> Come on, Frosti.
Go, Frosti.
>> PROBST: Frosti makes a
choice.
Let's find out if he's right.
Rat, ram, dragon, rooster, ram.
Rat, ram, dragon, rat is wrong.
Amanda has it wrong.
Rat, ram, dragon, rooster, ram.
Peih-Gee has it right.
That means Amanda, you can take
a seat.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: It comes down to
this.
Peih-Gee has it right.
Frosti, if you have it wrong,
Peih-Gee wins immunity.
>> I'm going crazy.
I'm losing my mind.
>> PROBST: Rat, ram, dragon,
rooster, ram is what you need to
have to stay alive.
Rat, ram, dragon, rooster, ram.
You got it right.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: You're still alive.
We are down to two-- immunity
and a guarantee of a one-in-
seven shot of winning this game.
Here we go.
Snake, rat, rabbit, tiger,
rooster, ram.
>> Come on, Frosti.
>> PROBST: Snake, rat, rabbit,
tiger, rooster, ram.
What are you upset about?
>> I don't know.
I think I lost my mind with
Frosti.
>> PROBST: Snake, rat, rabbit,
tiger, rooster, ram.
I think you got it right.
Peih-Gee has it right again.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Frosti, you have to
have it right to stay alive in
this.
Snake, the second one was rat.
You have rabbit.
It's over.
Peih-Gee wins immunity.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
And with that, stop eating.
Whatever you got in your mouth,
you can finish.
What's in your hands you need to
set down.
Give you a minute to swallow.
>> I'm covered in mayonnaise.
>> It's on your leg.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, the only
thing on day 27 better than a
cheeseburger is this right here.
>> That's right, baby.
>> PROBST: Individual immunity
guarantees you safe tonight at
tribal council, one-in-seven
shot at winning this game.
Frosti, Todd, Amanda, Erik,
Denise, Courtney, and James, one
of the seven you are going home
tonight.
See you at tribal.
Head on back.
>> How much did you guys eat?
>> I had two burgers and a ton
of fries and two things of cola.
And I hated myself for that.
>> It's hard to know that I took
a risk, made a sacrifice, and
nothing really came out of it.
I am upset that James, Denise,
Todd, and Courtney sat out.
Like, we're here for 12 more
days.
You can't wait 12 days for a
cheeseburger?
>> Frosti, you fought hard.
I did terrible.
>> Not winning immunity today
and having Peih-Gee win means
that we can't vote her out.
So I think Erik kind of already
knows that he's on the chopping
block.
>> Well, if I go tonight, good
luck to you.
>> If I go tonight, good luck to
you.
And we still didn't get
cheeseburgers.
>> Since Peih-Gee won immunity,
that means Frosti and I are kind
of the obvious ones to go, you
know, probably going to be one
of us.
And Frosti, I feel like he's...
somehow, you know, he's worked
his way... I think he's in good
with Todd and Amanda and
Courtney.
So it definitely makes it seem
like Frosti might be higher up
the ladder than he once was.
But then again, you know, I'm
tight with that group now.
So maybe that puts me up the
ladder as well.
So we'll see.
>> We have to be careful with
Erik, because he's not like
Peih-Gee.
He's not overbearing.
He's not abrasive.
But he's really good at
making... especially the girls.
>> He's smooth.
>> They love him.
>> And he plays up the good old
country boy from Tennessee.
>> I mean, he's a great guy.
And, like, he's awesome to have
around, but just got to be
careful.
>> It's like, "Here you go, have
a million dollars, Erik."
Tonight's vote's killer.
I mean, Erik, if he makes it to
the end, hands down, he's
guaranteed a million dollars.
But Frosti's a big threat.
You watch him perform in any of
the challenges, and he is great,
you know.
And that kind of worries me.
So I don't know what I'm going
to do.
It's a toss-up.
Frosti and Erik?
>> One of them guys is leaving.
>> Has to go.
We have to get rid of one of
those two.
I mean, I love Frosti.
I'll write his name down.
Courtney is really tight with
him.
If we have to, we pull her in to
get rid of Frosti.
She'll vote for Frosti.
>> I'm not sure you want to
trust her, though.
I mean, she thinks her Frosti's
with her.
>> Courtney...
>> We can convince Courtney.
>> You sure?
She's loving the hell out of
Frosti.
>> If she can't realize that, if
she really can't realize that,
maybe we should turn it around
and get rid of her.
>> The last tribal council we
went to, I thought everybody was
voting for Peih-Gee.
It turned out everybody was
voting for JR.
Tonight I really don't feel
paranoid, because at least I
think I know who everybody's
voting for.
It's either going to be Frosti
or it's going to be Courtney
that goes tonight.
>> Obviously, and it sucks, but
what are we at, eight?
Get rid of Erik or Frosti.
>> So Erik or Frosti.
>> Has to, right?
James and Denise are scared to
death that you would not be
willing to vote against Frosti.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah.
Yes.
And would you?
>> Frosti is kind of like my
little Munchkin, and you know,
everyone's kind of worried about
me because they know that he's,
you know, like, my good friend.
>> You've seen him compete.
I love the kid, but we don't
have a choice, right?
>> We'll see how it goes.
It really does, like,
strategically make a difference
whether or not, you know, I go
with the group on this one or I
don't go with the group on this
one.
So I don't know.
I mean, honestly, I don't know
who I'll vote for.
>> James and Denise were very
worried about Courtney and her
friendship with Frosti.
I'm worried.
I mean, we just don't know what
to expect.
She could literally take a sharp
turn right at any moment.
You know, I may have to vote for
her.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury, Jaime
and Jean-Robert, voted out at
the last tribal council.
Let's talk about today's
immunity challenge.
James, of all the people that
would choose to eat over
fighting for immunity, I have to
say you surprised me the most.
When you saw that plate of
cheeseburgers, what was your
initial thought?
>> Attack.
( laughter )
I ate seven of them.
>> PROBST: You ate set of the
12?
>> I ate seven burgers.
And I would have eaten that last
one.
I'm not playing.
I was hungry.
Yes, I have a strong ability to
win, and if I would have
competed, I would have competed
with my whole heart, but I'm
telling you, it was meat, man.
>> PROBST: Todd, you have a one-
in-even shot if you win today's
challenge, and yet you opted for
food.
>> The second you took the lid
off of those burgers and fries,
fat kid inside of Todd said,
"Food, eat, you are so hungry,"
you know?
And it's very risky putting
yourself in that situation,
especially when you tell
yourself you would never do it.
>> PROBST: Frosti, why did you
choose to not eat?
>> Well, I know that being here,
there's always a chance that you
could go home, no matter how
comfortable you feel, and that's
a chance that some people
decided to take.
But I want to know that I've
done everything I can to do my
best, to try my hardest, so that
if I do go home, I know that
it's not because I didn't do
everything I could.
>> PROBST: Erik, of the four
people that chose to sit out, do
you think it's a sign that they
are comfortable enough with
their status in the tribe that
they can eat and still be here
at the end of this tribal?
>> I knew I had to do the
challenge, so that definitely
draws a distinction between
where I am and where the people
that were eating are.
>> PROBST: Where are you in this
tribe?
>> I feel like I'm honestly
somewhere at the bottom, and
frankly, tonight I feel like I'm
very far at the bottom.
There's a chance I could make it
through tonight, but I'm not
necessarily planning on it.
>> PROBST: We're at a point in
the game where there are two
different types of
relationships: strategy
relationships, then
relationships that might extend
after the game.
Amanda, are those two
relationships starting to butt
heads yet when it comes to who
you vote out?
>> It's a hard thing, having
friendships and then trying to
play this game, because they
don't always follow the same
path.
So it's a hard thing to juggle.
>> PROBST: Denise, if you make a
friendship with somebody out
here, do you expect a little
more loyalty than somebody that
maybe they don't like?
>> I mean, you would hope that
the loyalty would be there, but
there is no loyalty in a game
like this.
There is no real down-to-the-
bottom trust.
I mean, it's a game.
I mean, you hope that the
friendships that you make and
the bonds that you create over
all this time will last in the
end.
>> PROBST: Frosti, what does it
say about you that you're still
here after being selected from
Fei Long presumably with the
idea to get rid of?
>> Well, I do believe that
forming the relationships that I
did with the whole tribe really
did help me.
And yes, sometimes you do have
to hurt people that you've
gotten close to.
But it is a game, and everyone
understands that.
And sometimes in games, people
get hurt.
>> PROBST: Erik, does it ever
feel personal?
>> Yeah.
I mean, it's hard, because I
feel like I've meant to make
friends too, and at some point,
there's only so much I can do,
you know, on the chopping block.
But of course, as far as, like,
trying to scheme and, like, get
myself in good with a select
few, although somewhat
necessary, also can be very
detrimental.
So I've really tried to be
careful, and you know, I have
very few options at this point
tonight, but....
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
get to the vote.
Peih-Gee, I don't even have to
ask.
I know you're not giving up that
necklace.
Peih-Gee is safe.
You cannot vote for Peih-Gee.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Todd, you're up.
>> One of us will be eating
cheeseburgers before the other.
Neither of us deserved it.
>> It's you and me tonight, bro.
Nothing personal.
>> I think you're an amazing
person.
I'm sorry.
I hope we can be friends later.
Bye.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
If anyone has the hidden
immunity idol, now is the time
to play it.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Frosti.
Erik.
Frosti.
Two votes Frosti, one vote Erik.
Three votes Frosti, one vote
Erik.
Frosti, it's four votes Frosti.
Ninth person voted out and the
third member of our jury,
Frosti.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Frosti, the tribe has spoken.
>> With cheeseburgers still on
their breath.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
Well, you've made it a long ways
in this game, but there are
still 12 days left.
Now, more than ever, the ability
to adapt moment to moment is
what's going to keep you in this
game.
We're going to test that right
now.
Tonight you will not be heading
directly back to camp.
We have more business to attend
to here.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, injuries take their
toll.
>> My knees are tore up.
>> PROBST: James is fed up.
>> You have to help me out.
I'm not doing all this stuff by
myself anymore.
They're going to pull the rope
with me, or they're all going to
die.
>> PROBST: And Todd takes a
stand.
>> I have a very, very strong
opinion, and I'm going to knock
you down if I have to.
You got to watch your mouth,
dude.
>> I expected some people to
kind of backstab, but I didn't
expect it right now.
I got beat by the tiny flight
attendant, the sassy New York
waitress, and the lady with the
mullet.
But you know, I wanted to prove
that somebody who is younger,
smaller could come out here and
do the same job that anyone else
can do, and I have proved that.