>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Peih-Gee picked Denise and Erik
to go with her on a reward to
the legendary Shaolin Temple...
...where Denise got to show
off her martial arts skills.
Back at camp, Amanda, Todd,
Courtney, and James made a final
four pact.
>> I've been the main guy trying
to hold this thing together, and
that's what I'm going to do.
>> PROBST: And because he had
both hidden immunity idols,
James was in the best position
to win it all.
At the immunity challenge...
Erik wins individual immunity.
...Erik a victory locked in
Peih-Gee as the next to go.
>> Get rid of Peih-Gee tonight,
and then after that focus on
getting rid of Erik, and then
it's all cake after that.
>> PROBST: But Amanda had other
ideas.
She hatched a plan to take out
James.
And everyone jumped at the
chance.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
James trusted his alliance...
Once the votes are read the
decision is final.
...so he didn't play one of his
idols.
Tenth person voted out, and the
fourth member of our jury,
James.
By failing to recognize he was
in danger, the most powerful
player in the game was gone,
taking the idols with him.
James, the tribe has spoken.
Six are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I think that was the most
shocking tribal council yet.
I think that Jean-Robert got a
big kick out of James getting
voted out.
>> I think so, too.
>> He was like, "Do-do-do, they
got you, do-do-do."
>> "Wow," is all I have to say
about tribal council.
I was so nervous that idea
wouldn't work to vote James out,
and it did.
I wonder how mad James is right
now.
>> Lord, have mercy.
What did you say?
I was like, "I hope to god this
doesn't turn into a screaming
match back at the camp."
>> I said, "If this works, wow.
If it doesn't, I'm scared for my
life."
>> If it doesn't work and he
comes back here, I was like,
"Oh, my god, could you imagine
if he came back here?"
We would all be dead.
>> James is gone.
He didn't use the idols.
I'm still here.
I had a vote cast against me.
My heart was pounding.
We are in the top six.
>> How about we celebrate we are
in the top six?
>> Yay!
>> We'll bitch a little bit
tomorrow.
It will probably rain.
It will probably rain again.
>> Group hug, everybody.
>> Where is Peih-Gee?
Where is Peih-Gee?
>> Seeing original Fei Long
members turn on each other
absolutely gives me hope.
There must be a crack old tribal
lines somewhere, because Erik
and I are still around.
>> Peeg, you and your Buddha
outfit.
You're tripping me out.
>> If I can get one or maybe
even two more people, we could
possibly cause a tie at tribal
council, which would be kind of
interesting.
I'm not giving up until I'm
voted out.
You know, I love it that I'm
still here.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Seems like we've been here
for years.
♪ What am I doing here? ♪
>> All I really want is a beer.
>> This is so crazy.
I can't even describe to you how
miserable I feel.
I have thought of home for the
past week and a half and how
much I miss it.
You know, I'm not an emotional
person at all, but it kills you,
kills you-- oh, man.
So close.
>> We've got a week left.
Somebody has a week left.
>> Seven nights and six days.
>> And one poor unfortunate
soul...
>> ...is going to go home.
>> ...will be taken out of the
rain.
My alliance in the game is me,
Courtney, Amanda, and Denise.
We want to get rid of Erik and
Peih-Gee.
That is the goal.
But at the same time, you can't
trust anybody 100% because in
all reality, we all want one
million dollars.
And if they turn on me, it would
be a very smart move on their
part to get rid of me now.
Of course, I'm not going to tell
them that.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
reward challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge is
all about speed and
communication.
Here's how it works-- for
today's challenge, you will be
paired up in teams of two.
Each team will be separated at
opposite ends of a maze.
On my "go," you must navigate
your way through the maze, find
your partner, and make your way
to the center platform.
First team it get there wins.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: To make it a bit more
interesting, you'll be
blindfolded.
Should we get you paired up?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: All right, Erik,
you're going to be paired up
with your mom.
>> What?
>> PROBST: Come on out, Denise.
Don't be shy.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Is this really happening?
>> Look at you!
>> Yeah, I'm all skinny and
bearded.
>> PROBST: Denise, take a spot
over here.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Amanda, here's your
partner, your sister, Katrina.
>> Oh, my god!
Oh!
>> How are you?
>> That's okay.
I think I can forgive you.
>> PROBST: All right, Katrina.
Peih-Gee, here's somebody who
loves you very much-- your dad,
Lawrence.
>> It's my dad.
Oh, my god!
>> Hi, Peih-Gee!
Let me look at you.
My god, you're skinny!
>> It's a good weight loss
program.
Okay.
>> PROBST: Todd, you ready for
some love?
Your sister Brandy's here.
Come on out, Brandy!
Brandy's not going to walk.
That's a hug.
>> Okay, okay.
I'm so glad you're here.
How is everybody?
>> Good.
>> Kim's good, right?
Is the baby okay?
Okay.
>> PROBST: Todd what was the
last question?
>> My little sister was
pregnant, and she lost her baby,
but it's okay.
>> PROBST: Your other sister?
>> Yeah.
One a little bit younger than
Brandy.
So...
>> PROBST: So, Brandy, the
message you gave Todd is that
your sister lost the baby, but
your sister herself is doing
all right.
>> She's doing good.
She's doing good.
>> That's all that matters.
It's okay.
>> PROBST: Courtney, I know
you're ready for some love.
Here's your daddy Graham.
Looking debonair.
>> I told you he'd wear a suit.
>> I'm English.
I don't do... I don't do shorts.
>> He's English.
>> PROBST: All right, guys.
Graham, take a spot.
>> Thank you.
Thanks.
>> PROBST: Denise, I think
there's somebody back there
really anxious to see you-- your
husband.
Come on out, Robert!
>> Yeah!
>> You want them?
I'll give them to you.
>> PROBST: She was going to drag
you all the way over there.
All right, let me catch the
loved ones up on what the
survivors already know, which is
you are not just here to bring
them love.
You are going to participate in
this challenge.
>> I'm sorry, dad.
I didn't know.
They didn't tell me!
I'm sorry!
>> PROBST: Today, you are
playing for a boat trip out on
the lake, a huge meal, and love
in the form of a phone call from
family members back home.
The winning team will receive
this Sprint phone.
Sprint, also known for speed and
communication, is making this
all possible.
Shall we get started?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: You guys head off
this way.
You head off this way.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors and loved ones ready?
Go!
First pair of survivor and loved
one to reach the platform wins
reward.
>> Rob, where are you?!
>> Coming at you.
>> Coming at me, all right, here
we go.
>> Okay, Amanda, where are you
at?
>> Katrina, that's me.
>> Mom, where are you?
>> I'm over here.
>> Are you somewhere near the
center?
>> I have no idea.
>> PROBST: Some loved ones
getting close, others still very
far away.
>> Lawrence, dad, where are you?
Lawrence?
>> I hear you, Peih-Gee.
I can't get to you.
It's a dead end over there.
>> I'm in the center, Brandy.
Where are you at?
>> I'm not sure.
I'm over here somewhere.
>> Katrina!
>> Amanda!
>> Denise, I'm towards the
middle.
>> Rob, I hear you, where are
you?
>> I'm close.
Where are you at?
>> Right here, right here, but
I'm stuck.
>> PROBST: Denise and Robert
have connected.
They've still got to make their
way to the center platform.
>> Todd!
>> I'm coming to your voice,
stay cool.
>> Bloody nose, bloody
nose.
( making bird calls )
>> PROBST: Amanda and Katrina
communicating like wild birds.
>> Stop that noise.
>> Peih-Gee!
>> Yeah, I hear you, dad, right
here, Lawrence.
>> I'm right here.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee has found
her dad, Lawrence.
>> This direction, over there.
>> PROBST: Lawrence trying to
point her in the right
direction.
That's not going to help when
you can't see.
>> Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, Daddy,
Daddy!
Where the hell are you?
Courtney still looking for her
father.
>> Oh, stop it, Probst.
>> Look, we're going to go
around the circle, find the
opening on the other side of
this.
>> PROBST: Denise and her
husband are working together,
trying to find their way to the
center platform.
( making bird calls )
>> I'm here!
>> All the way around.
Just keep going.
>> PROBST: Denise and Robert
getting very close to winning
this challenge.
Denise is paired up with Robert.
They're looking for the steps.
Denise and Robert win reward!
>> Whoo!
>> Yeah, Denise!
Yeah!
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfolds.
It's over.
All right, Denise and Robert.
Here's what's going to happen--
you're going to go out on a
boat.
You're going to have a nice
meal.
I'm going to turn this Sprint
phone on right now, because
you're going to get a phone
call.
Keep this phone turned on.
In addition, you're going to
choose two survivors to come
along with you and bring their
loved ones.
Who's the first survivor that
you're going to bring along with
their loved one?
>> Todd.
>> PROBST: Todd and his sister,
Brandy, are going with you.
Denise, you look pained to have
to make another decision.
>> This is a very tough decision
for me, Jeff.
I'm sorry, I'm going to have to
go with Amanda.
>> PROBST: Amanda and her sister
going on the reward.
>> Thank you!
Thank you so much.
>> PROBST: All right, the good
part of the reward is over.
Now comes the tough part.
Time for you guys to say good-
bye to your loved ones.
>> Good-bye.
>> Thanks for coming.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: All right, Lawrence.
>> PROBST: All right, Erik,
Peih-Gee, Courtney, grab your
stuff, head back to camp.
>> Have fun, guys.
>> PROBST: Okay, there is one
more element to this reward.
When the afternoon is over, the
loved ones are going to spend
the night at your camp.
They're going to get a chance to
experience what you've been
living for 31 days.
Boat's waiting for you.
Have fun.
>> Oh, my god, there's ribs.
Oh, look at the chicken.
There's pizza.
>> There's pizza?
Are you serious?
>> Guys, dig in.
>> We have been eating off the
ground, literally.
>> Rip it apart.
>> You have never seen me eat
like this, have you?
>> Oh, my god.
>> How is it, honey?
Just for my husband to be here
in China... he's afraid to fly.
Just for him to come here, that
means a lot to me.
But to come here and compete and
to win a challenge together,
it's so uplifting.
I've been taken over the top.
>> Ah!
Oh, my god!
>> Oh, look at that!
>> That's Todd's piece right
there.
>> Do you want some?
>> Oh, hell, yeah, baby.
>> This is best chocolate cake I
have ever had in my life.
( phone ringing )
>> Your phone's ringing.
>> There's my call, hon.
>> There they are, look!
>> Say hello.
>> Hello?
>> Hi.
>> All of a sudden I can hear
people crying in the background.
And it's my oldest daughter,
Erin.
>> Don't cry.
You've got to talk to me.
How did you guys do in the
tournament?
All right!
Daddy's here with me.
>> And I smell so bad.
>> Can you smell me from there?
>> Smell-a-vision.
>> I'm smiling just thinking
about you, sweet pea.
I think about you every day.
No, don't cry.
I miss you so much.
>> I love you, too.
You have a good night, okay?
And I'll see you really, really
soon.
>> I love you.
Good night, baby.
Being able to hear their voices
and have my husband here with me
today, it gives me the strength,
definitely, to keep on going,
and, I mean, I'm here to the
end.
I'm going to grab strength from
them and embrace it and just
keep on going.
>> I wonder why Denise picked
Amanda.
I'll be honest, I'm kind of
pissed that she didn't pick me,
because I took her off on a fat
reward.
>> I've got to get this off my
chest-- I do not believe Todd's
story.
>> I could not believe that
he... like, "Oh, my sister had
an unplanned teenage pregnancy,
and then a convenient
miscarriage."
Gee whiz.
You think the girl might not
want the entire world to know
about that.
>> Like, if it's true, my
deepest condolences to his
family.
>> I thought the same thing.
I was like, "Oh, how
convenient."
And then he was the first one
picked by Denise.
Right.
Todd was going for the Oscar
with his performance of "My
sister had a convenient
miscarriage."
And then of course Jeff was
like, "Todd, it looks like you
just got some bad news.
What happened?"
And Todd's like "My sister.
She was pregnant and she... she
lost the baby.
But it happened for a reason."
Like, that is not, like the fake
Johnny Fair Play, "My grandma
died."
You can almost forgive that.
That's funny.
>> What is that?
>> Shut up!
>> Indulge, kids!
Indulge!
>> Kinky!
>> When the loved ones showed
up, you know, we were
sourpusses.
We were pissed that we lost the
challenge, pissed we didn't get
to go.
I really didn't feel like
interacting with anybody.
>> I'm so bad with names.
Mr. Denise...
>> It's Robert.
>> So how proud are you of
Denise?
>> Very, very proud.
>> It was really tough.
And especially for me.
Like, I picked Denise to go with
me on a literally once-in-a-
lifetime reward trip, and, you
know, she didn't pick me.
And it sucks.
>> Amanda, how perfect it is
that we...
>> I know!
>> I can't believe it.
>> Really, we're just so lucky
that Denise got to pick two
people and she chose us.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> So surreal.
>> And the other thing that
scared me was when I whispered
about Kim, you know, I was like,
"They're going to think I'm
lying, like I'm pulling a big
lie to see my sister."
Hopefully everybody believes it
because it wasn't a lie.
>> I'm so sorry about that.
>> You know, I know there's been
a lot of pointing at me as to a
strategic threat, but it was all
true.
It was all from the heart, you
know?
I wasn't out to be some snake
right there.
I really was concerned about my
home.
>> How pregnant was she?
>> She was about two months.
>> Three months now.
>> She lost it a while ago,
Todd.
>> Did she?
>> Yeah.
>> Like, right after I left?
>> Pretty much.
>> Seems like you're getting
along all right.
>> Yeah, know, everybody seems
to be okay.
You know, I mean, like I said,
there's a lot of young kids
here, and I don't have a lot in
common with them.
But we'll see what happens.
I mean, I can only hope that
Amanda and Todd stay with me,
and we go to the final three.
If they backstab me and take
Courtney, that's one of the
chances I'm going to have to
take.
But, I mean, to be out here all
this time is still pretty damn
good.
>> Yeah.
Play your game, that's all.
Do what you... do what you think
is right.
>> I mean, obviously, it's not a
good idea for us to backstab
anyone anymore, but I think as
long as we take Denise to the
final four she'll understand.
>> Would you vote out Denise
before Courtney, or no?
>> Yeah.
>> Because we can win better...
>> She works hard all week.
I mean, she has kids.
>> I freaking love Denise.
I do.
>> The thing is, in the final
three, she will play her sob
story.
>> That's right.
We... like, Amanda, and I and
Courtney are all pretty much on
the same level, because we've
pissed a lot of the people on
the jury off.
And so, like, it's a pretty even
chance between all of us.
So I'm like...
>> And we would make such a cute
final three.
>> Oh, you guys can do this.
>> Yeah.
>> You got it.
>> Perfect.
>> It's like a dream.
>> I know you'll do good.
>> I'm going to do my best.
>> Easily into the one or two
spot.
You know what you're doing.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I love you.
My god, you smell bad.
>> I know.
I'm so sorry.
I stink.
>> I've got to smell just as
bad, though.
>> You're getting there, honey.
You're fitting right in with
this group, I tell you.
>> 32 days.
I can make it a few more.
Tell everyone I miss them, okay?
>> I love you.
>> See you in a few days, okay?
>> It kills you to say good-bye
to loved ones, but you can't
stop the game, because the game
keeps going.
So you want to feel comfortable,
and you want to feel like you
can trust people, and you just
can't, though.
You've got to keep on your toes.
You've got to keep yourself
nervous, or else you're going to
get screwed.
>> No, I know.
I could see it, you know.
It wasn't my fault.
You know, it just happened to
work out that way.
I don't want to be the next one
to go.
>> After the loved ones left,
Denise came over and
tried to kind of fix that little
problem that she might have with
me, like, not getting picked.
>> I do feel a little better
that at least she took the time
to come talk to me.
I might need her vote if I can
convince her to try to vote
somebody else off.
>> I mean, I just wanted to see
where you're standing, and I
wanted you to see where I'm
coming from, you know what I
mean?
>> Right now I'm going to
concentrate on gathering up all
my energy and focus on winning
that challenge, because I really
need it.
Every time since the merge, I
feel like I need to win.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Erik, give it up.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
You are going to have to dig
deep, as today's challenge will
test you both physically and
mentally.
For today's challenge, you'll be
attached to a rope which snakes
through a series of obstacles.
At each obstacle, you must
untangle your rope by either
moving over, under, or around
each post in order to continue.
At the end of the course, you'll
find a set of boxes.
Each box contains one true and
one false statement about
Chinese inventions.
Next to each statement is a key.
Choose the statement you think
is true, grab the key, race back
to the start.
If you're right, your key will
open a lock.
If you're wrong, you have to go
back and try again.
First person to answer three
questions correctly and open
three locks will raise their
flag.
First person to raise their flag
wins immunity, guaranteed a one-
in-five shot at winning this
game.
We'll get started.
Head up on the deck.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You are attached to a rope that
runs the length of this course.
Erik flies over.
Amanda's over.
Todd making quick work of it.
Denise is over.
Todd and Amanda making their way
through the swamp.
Peih-Gee's right there.
Todd first up the mountain.
Amanda right behind.
Erik snagged on one of the
posts.
It's Todd and Amanda in the
lead.
Todd and Amanda both untying
their first box.
There are two statements.
One is true, one is false.
Todd has his first key.
Amanda has her first key.
Peih-Gee's made her first
choice.
Todd going to pass Erik as he
heads to the start.
Amanda heading back to the start
with her first key.
Peih-Gee heading back into the
swamp with her first key.
Big question for Todd-- did he
choose the true statement?
Will the key open a lock?
And it does.
Todd has his first lock open.
Todd and Amanda both have one
lock undone.
Two locks left.
Courtney struggling to get back
with her first key.
Erik trying to get back in it.
Todd still in the lead.
Amanda right behind.
Peih-Gee back with her first
key.
Peih-Gee has her first lock
open.
She's heading back for her
second.
Todd, Amanda, Peih-Gee, all have
one lock open.
Denise and Erik struggling to
stay in it.
Todd at his second box.
Amanda at her second box.
Choose the one you think is true
and grab the key.
Amanda and Todd both with their
second keys.
Erik trying to stay in this
challenge for immunity.
First lock doesn't open.
Second lock doesn't open.
Third lock doesn't open.
Erik now in dead last.
Todd and Amanda neck and neck as
they head back into the swamp.
Peih-Gee heading back with her
second key.
Todd opens his second lock.
Todd has only one lock left.
Amanda trying her key in the
first lock.
It does not work.
Trying it in the remaining lock.
This gives Todd a huge lead.
Peih-Gee back with her second
key.
Did she choose right?
She did.
It's Peih-Gee and Todd with two
locks open, one lock left.
Amanda still fighting, hoping
Todd will make a mistake.
Peih-Gee right on Todd's tail.
Todd has two statements left.
If he chooses the true statement
he'll have his third and final
key.
Todd has made his choice.
The question is, did he choose
the right statement?
Peih-Gee now opening her third
box.
You want a guarantee you go
final five, you keep fighting.
Peih-Gee has made her choice.
Todd and Peih-Gee both have
their third keys.
With that third key in hand, if
he is right, Todd wins immunity.
If he's wrong, it oppose the
door for Peih-Gee.
It does not open.
It's taken every bit of strength
Peih-Gee has left to get back
with that third key.
If she's right, it was worth it.
If she answered correctly, she
will open the lock.
She does.
And with that, Peih-Gee wins
immunity!
Peih-Gee, come on over.
>> I never would have believed
it.
>> PROBST: For the second time,
Peih-Gee wins individual
immunity.
You are safe tonight at tribal
council, guaranteed a spot in
the final five.
Denise, Todd, Courtney, Amanda,
Erik, after 33 days, this game
will come to an end for one of
you.
See you tonight at tribal
council.
Head on back to camp.
>> You know, honestly, like, I
can't believe I won.
I'm still crying about it.
Wow.
I've been, like, underdog this
whole time I've been here.
Every council that I'm not
wearing the necklace, I expect
to be voted out, you know, so...
>> Erik, come to the table.
The muddy rice is ready.
>> This is probably one of, like
my proudest moments, like, I've
ever had in my entire life.
I'm safe tonight, but it's been,
like, really mentally and
physically exhausting.
>> I'm okay.
The only thing that would be a
surprise is if Amanda would
turn.
But she won't, because she knows
if Erik or Peih-Gee get even
close to the end, they've got
it.
So...
It seemed so obvious to me, at
least, when Peih-Gee won
immunity, who else is going to
go tonight?
Erik.
It's probably the easiest vote
for me so far.
>> I feel like, even if I were
on Todd's side, I would feel a
little shaded out, just by not
trusting him with, like, that...
what I think is false
information about his sister.
>> He could very well have,
like, played that up as, you
know, a way to get further in
the game.
It's what it sounded like to me,
too.
>> The hard part for me is that
nobody here trusts Todd.
It irks me, because I've thrown
his name out, and it's like,
"Okay, well, if you don't trust
him, then what's the deal?"
I feel like I have to fight.
But I don't know what to do.
>> Thanks.
>> I'll talk to Denise.
>> My plan for tonight, is Erik
and I are going to vote for
Todd, and hope that Denise
swings for a tie.
>> If she votes Erik out now,
it's highly likely she'll end up
in fourth place.
If she tries to force a tie and
Todd gets voted out tonight,
suddenly her chances of getting
to top three are much better.
>> I will.
Denise isn't stupid, though.
>> This tribal council right
here is definitely a turning
point in the game.
If I do switch and head to that
side of the coin, are my chances
better?
Probably.
But am I going to win against
one of those two?
I don't know.
I mean, it's just... right now
it's, like, a 50-50 split.
>> Oh, that cold wind.
I hate that cold wind.
That means it's about to start
in my...
>> I trust you, I do.
>> I'm definitely the swing vote
tonight.
For me, personally, I mean, this
is do or die.
When I get up there, I mean, I
don't know right now who I'm
going to pick.
What happens when I come back to
camp after I make this decision?
Who's going to be flipping out?
This is a game for a million
dollars, and right now, writing
someone's name down is a
million-dollar signature.
>> It's going to be the longest
wait of my life.
>> I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little scared.
I'm a little in turmoil.
I'm a little flipping out.
Thunder and lightning is getting
closer, the decision's getting
closer, my mind is racing.
This is just insane.
I don't know.
I just don't know what to do.
Can you help me?
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Jaime, Jean-Robert, Frosti, and
James, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Let's talk about the reward
challenge.
Amanda, after spending the
afternoon with Denise and seeing
her and her husband interact,
did you feel like you knew
Denise in a different way?
>> Oh, definitely.
I think she's blessed with a
great life-- like, a great
family, a great bond with her
kids.
It was just nice to see that
part of Denise, like the softer
side of Denise.
>> PROBST: Denise, is there a
downside to everybody seeing
what a great life you have?
>> Oh, definitely.
I mean, it's a two-way street--
yes, it's a good thing to let
them see a little bit, but it's
bad because maybe they won't
vote for me, or maybe they feel
a little scared to let me go
against them in the finals.
>> PROBST: Why would they not
want to go against you in the
finals?
>> I don't know if they would
vote for someone who already has
a good, experienced life, and
give them a million dollars.
You know, maybe I'll get a
sympathy vote or maybe I'll get
more votes on the jury because
of that.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, for the
last several tribal councils,
it's either going to have been
you or Erik voted out.
What's your take on tonight's
vote?
Do you think there is a strong
consensus of what's going to
happen, or do you think there's
a lot of ambiguity going on?
>> I think there's definitely
some ambiguity going on.
You know, if you want to look at
it as us being two against four,
one person is at the very
bottom.
And I don't see why they would
make that leap and be like, "I
don't want to be fourth.
I want to be first, possibly."
It could turn the game around
entirely for one or two people,
you know, and so it's something
that everybody's going to have
to take into consideration very
carefully.
>> PROBST: Denise, does the talk
of the vote being up in the air
concern you?
>> Yeah.
I mean, there's three people
over there, there's two people
here, and I mean, I always feel
like I'm on the bottom of the
barrel.
Yeah, I'm really, really scared.
But I mean, hopefully tonight's
the night that I can trust
people.
So to get a little further in
the game would be great.
I want to stay here for as long
as I can.
So, I mean, I'm just going to
hope for the best.
>> PROBST: Todd, is there
anybody here that you trust?
>> Yes, I do trust people here.
I have to, because I'm not
wearing that necklace.
So I feel like I do trust
people, yeah.
I just don't know exactly 100%
how much.
>> PROBST: Erik, if it's you
tonight, have you done
everything you can to try and
crack this other four?
>> Yeah.
Honestly, like, I want... I want
to be here tomorrow.
And I hope people realize if
there's four and two, there
could be three and three, and
all of a sudden you're not
fourth.
You're in the top three and
you've got a chance to win the
million dollars.
And I'm playing that card.
I mean that is... that is all
I've got left.
>> PROBST: Let's get to the
vote.
Peih-Gee, you have individual
immunity.
You can give it up, if you want.
You cannot vote for Peih-Gee.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
>> It's either going to be me or
you tonight.
I'm not ready to go.
So...
>> Too many people said they
couldn't trust you.
Sorry.
>> I'm sorry I have to do this.
This is probably the biggest
mistake I'm going to make in
this game.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Erik.
Todd.
One vote Erik, one vote Todd.
Two votes Todd, one vote Erik.
Erik.
Two votes Erik, two votes Todd.
That's three votes Erik, two
votes Todd, one vote left.
11th person voted out, and the
fifth member of our jury, Erik.
You need to bring me your torch.
Erik, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> PROBST: Well, based on what I
heard tonight, it sound like
you're all battling the same
question-- "Do I take somebody
with me simply because I think I
can beat them or do I take with
me somebody I think is most
deserving because I showed I
wanted to beat the best?"
It could be a million dollar
decision.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> Are we getting extreme
Survivor paranoia right now?
>> PROBST: Amanda targets Todd.
>> I could pull Peih-Gee and
Denise together.
>> PROBST: But Todd fights back.
>> An angry Todd is a bad Todd.
>> I will be pissed off.
>> PROBST: As alliances crumble,
no one is safe.
>> I hope you guys vote to knock
off Todd.
I'd like to see that happen.
>> I wanted to go all the way to
the top in this game, but,
unfortunately, today was my day.
I think I can always look back
and say, "Well, I could have
done this differently or I could
have done that," but I'm
mentally and physically and
emotionally exhausted.
I made it 33 days.
I'm really proud of myself.
The five remaining contestants
are going to battle it out, and
I'm really curious to see who
comes out on top.