>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> Oh, wow!
>> PROBST: At Zhan Hu, Dave's
tribe mates urged him to stop
working and save his strength
for the challenges.
>> I just want you to conserve
your energy because I do not
want to lose another challenge.
>> Peih-gee.
(makes kissing sound)
>> PROBST: Sherea and Jaime
taking on Amanda.
Amanda is in the water.
After losing four challenges in
a row, Sherea finally led the
Zhan Hu tribe to victory...
Zhan Hu wins their first
challenge!
... giving them the right to
kidnap a member of the other
tribe.
Who are you going to steal?
>> Leslie.
>> PROBST: Leslie.
At Zhan Hu, Leslie bonded with
her fellow Christians.
>> I'm misunderstood over in
my tribe.
My faith is everything.
>> PROBST: And she gave Jaime a
clue to the hidden immunity
idol.
At Fei Long, poker player
Jean-Robert continued to
bluff his tribe mates by acting
weak and tired.
>> Later on, when I am
contributing, people are
noticing, "Hey, this guy is
doing beyond his normal
capability."
>> PROBST: Go.
At the immunity challenge, Fei
Long was frustrated because
Courtney was too weak to hack
it.
>> How are they doing this?
>> PROBST: And Sherea was the
hero again, pulling Zhan Hu to
their second straight victory.
Zhan Hu wins immunity!
With Fei Long facing their first
tribal council, Courtney
attempted to save herself by
targeting Jean-Robert.
>> I think if he goes and I
stay, then it will be different.
>> It's a very friendly tribe.
Three of them are Christian,
which is, I think, why they
picked me.
>> PROBST: But the alliance of
Aaron, Todd and Amanda grew
worried about Leslie's bond with
the other tribe.
>> I just feel Leslie is more
dangerous than Jean-Robert.
We need to take her out.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
the alliance got their way.
Jean-Robert and Courtney were
spared...
Third person voted out of
Survivor: China.
...and Leslie was voted out.
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Is it too early for us to
put the water on?
>> No.
>> No?
>> No, as soon as it starts to
get hot.
>> I thought there was a small
chance I could go home last
night, but I figured I'd be
staying.
I'm a professional poker player.
And my game plan is starting to
kick in.
I'm one of those guys who likes
to start out in last place.
I was the last horse.
Now, I'm just slowly edging up
on the pack, and I've kicked ass
in the challenges, and my work
ethic in the camp has improved,
and people notice that.
>> You're like sucking it up
already.
It's, like, 6:00 in the morning.
>> Getting past last night's
vote was big, but at the next
tribal council, I'm not that
worried, either, because
Courtney is always the weak
link in every challenge.
And if she survives the next
tribal council, she's got to be
the luckiest girl in Survivor
history.
>> I was afraid it might be hot.
>> I was trying to protect you.
>> I'm not getting mad at you,
so you don't need to get huffy.
Waking up with Jean-Robert
still here is just how I knew
it would be.
He's a cocky son of a bitch,
and he sucks so bad, there's no
getting out of that.
>> That was like a cautionary,
like, "Careful."
>> I understand, but just so
you know where I'm coming from,
I have a gut reaction, I don't
like anyone raising their voice
to me.
I don't give a crap who goes
next, as long as it's not me.
I would prefer it be
Jean-Robert because he's just so
unpleasant and he gets in my
face with no matter what I say.
He's just aggressive with me,
and I'm sick of it.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS and PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> Is it really wet on the
bottom?
>> Oh, no.
>> It's kind of stinky.
>> This morning, we discovered
a large portion of our rice has
mold on it.
That's bad news.
So, we tried to separate out
the good stuff before it gets
worse.
>> Before you pick it up and
start mixing up that gunge over
again, we need to put it in
something else and toss the
moldy stuff.
>> What do you suggest we put
it in?
>> I don't know, man.
Find something.
Think of something.
>> Great, you can get that.
I'm not eating mold!
>> Okay, great, you ask for
everything.
You are not running the show up
in here.
People have ideas, too.
>> Thanks for listening, Sherea.
>> Same way you do with
everybody else.
You just listen, listen, listen,
right?
I don't think so.
You want everybody to listen
to you, but you don't listen to
nobody else, so shut... stop
talking to me, please.
>> Sherea, she just came
unglued on me.
You know, you've got some
grounds to say those kind of
things if you've done more
around camp.
I'm doing my best to be a good
leader.
So, it's frustrating.
>> Sherea!
Please do not throw those away.
>> I wish you wouldn't touch
me.
>> Please don't do that.
I'm saving some of these shells!
>> Back up off me!
Back up off me.
Back the (no audio) up off me.
>> Why...
>> I swear to God, back up off
me.
>> Why won't you give me some
of the shells?
>> Back up off me.
>> She won't let me keep the
shells!
>> The last day or so, Dave, I
mean, he's been digging himself
a grave further and further and
further.
>> My God, I just asked to save
a few of these things so I can
take them back to my mom, you
know.
>> He's just very condescending
the way he talks to people.
But nobody is going to run over
me, talk to me any kind of way.
>> I'm not so hot on Sherea
right now because she's holding
on to stuff that I'm not.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And everyone else is on
eggshells, I think, more
because of Sherea than me right
now.
>> People right now are seeing
you as something who's just
going off all the time.
I do admit you've given a lot
of great stuff to this tribe
and we wouldn't be the tribe
that we are without you.
We just have to make sure that
if you're going to be a
leader...
Dave's put himself in a weird
position with everybody.
I mean, he does help around
camp but he's also pissing
people off.
So Crazy Dave may have just
worn out his welcome.
>> Tree mail!
Let's go!
>> Is it tonight?
>> Tribal council.
>> Tribal council?
>> What?
>> Oh, boy!
>> "Tonight, both tribes go to
tribal council, where fire
represents your life.
In the shadows of the temple,
the winners earn less strife.
This doesn't require lots of
brawn, but if you're not agile,
you'll take a beating.
Only the tribe who can stick
together tomorrow will be
eating."
>> I don't think so.
I think it's just at the tribal
council.
>> Food!
>> Oh, my God, you guys.
We have got to win this!
>> Let's win this food, brother.
I'm thrilled about this tree
mail because they're talking
about food.
I'm a pretty big eater already,
and the last three days I've
virtually eaten nothing.
So, for me it's not just
exciting, it's, like,
necessary.
I need to eat something.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Zhan Hu getting your first look
at the new Fei Long tribe.
Leslie voted out the last
tribal council.
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
(applause)
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, two tribe members at
a time will use giant chopsticks
to carry a fireball across the
course, drop it down a chute
into a wok, igniting a firework
display.
You'll then race back to the
start.
The next two go.
Each round, the chopsticks will
get longer and more difficult
to handle.
First tribe to get all three
fireballs into all three woks
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Tomorrow morning, a
fisherman and his family will
come to your camp and teach you
to fish.
They will bring with them
spices, vegetables, make you a
meal.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will kidnap one
member from the losing tribe.
That person will stay with them
until the next immunity
challenge.
Fei Long, because you have one
extra member, you're sitting
one person out.
Keeping in mind you cannot sit
out same person in back-to-back
challenges, who are you going
to sit out in this one?
>> We're going to sit out
Courtney.
>> PROBST: Courtney's going to
sit this one out.
Courtney, take a spot on the
bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
The first two for Zhan Hu,
Peih-gee and Sherea.
For Fei Long, it's Todd and
Denise.
For reward, survivors ready?
Go.
Got to light the ball and then
pick it up.
Sherea and Peih-gee working
together.
Denise and Todd working
>> There you go.
Nice.
>> PROBST: Each person has one
chopstick.
You have to figure out how to
work together.
>> Go on the other side, Sherea.
Go parallel, parallel.
>> Go slow.
>> PROBST: Denise and Todd
making a little progress.
>> Cross under.
>> PROBST: Can't push the ball.
Got to pick it up.
Sherea and Peih-gee had it
going for a moment.
Todd and Denise doing very well.
Peih-gee and Sherea getting the
hang of it now.
>> There you go, guys!
>> PROBST: Peih-gee and Sherea
work together.
Peih-gee and Sherea gaining on
them now.
Todd and Denise very close.
No!
They drop it just short of the
chute.
Peih-gee and Sherea very close.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Todd and Denise have
their first ball down the chute.
They're heading back!
Peih-gee and Sherea still
working on that first fireball.
They have it for Zhan Hu, and
they race back!
Amanda and Aaron, working
together now on that second
ball for Fei Long.
It's Jaime and Frosti now for
Zhan Hu, working on that second
fireball.
The longer the chopsticks get,
the more difficult they are to
handle.
>> Up, up.
>> PROBST: Frosti having to
maneuver with the flames
hitting his hands, burning him.
They're on the wrong side of
that flame box.
Amanda and Aaron working
together, moving slowly but
making ground.
>> A little bit at a time.
>> PROBST: Jaime and Frosti
still in it.
Both tribes even with one ball.
Aaron and Amanda doing a great
job.
Jamie and Frosti trying to gain
on them.
Aaron and Amanda have the big
task now of getting up high
enough to drop it in the chute.
Aaron and Amanda have it.
They have their second one for
Fei Long.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Amy and Frosti close.
Jamie and Frosti have the
second ball for Zhan Hu.
We are dead even.
James and Jean-Robert working on
the third and final ball for Fei
Long.
>> These sticks are impossible!
>> Just focus, man.
This is not impossible.
>> I got it, I got it.
>> PROBST: It's Dave and Erik
now for Zhan Hu.
James and Jean-Robert making a
little progress.
Dave and Erik working with
those long chopsticks, much
more difficult.
>> Ah!
>> Go forward with it!
You have to move at least an
inch every time!
>> PROBST: Dave and Erik getting
a lot of advice from their
tribe.
It's not helping.
James and Jean-Robert getting
closer.
Big reward on the line-- fish,
vegetables, spices.
Dave and Erik are going to have
to do something heroic.
Jean-Robert and James very
close.
This could be it.
Jean-Robert, so close.
>> Dave, get low!
Dave, get low!
>> Go at the same time.
>> PROBST: James and Jean-Robert
so close.
Trying to hang on.
Almost had it.
Opening the door for Erik and
Dave.
A few inches at a time, they
are gaining on James and
Jean-Robert.
>> Lift it like this.
>> PROBST: Next fireball down
the chute wins.
This could be it for Fei Long.
And it is!
(cheers)
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Fei Long wins reward!
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, Fei Long,
congratulations.
(applause)
You're now going to kidnap one
member of Zhan Hu's tribe.
Who's it going to be?
>> Dave or Jaime.
It doesn't matter.
>> It's Dave.
>> PROBST: Dave, head on over.
You are going to spend time
with Fei Long.
Dave, you will remain with Fei
Long until the next immunity
challenge.
All right, Dave, this is for
you.
You know the drill.
It says, "open in private."
That means private and alone.
Zhan Hu, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> See you, folks.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: All right, guys, grab
your flag.
Head on back to camp.
Enjoy tomorrow.
(laughs)
>> Yeah!
Escargot, dawg.
>> Oh, man, I feel like I'm on
vacation right now.
It's just absolutely wonderful.
I'm going to eat well with
them today.
And given the friction between
Sherea and I, I couldn't ask
for a better time to be
kidnapped.
Good morning, everybody.
What you eating on there?
>> You're right, you're right.
I apologize.
Some of my tribe are definitely
threatening to me, and that
means I'm going to have to be
aligned with other people.
So it is a spy mission, but
it's a spy mission for me.
>> "In this sealed tube is a
clue to a hidden immunity
idol.
You must give this sealed clue
to a member of this tribe
before you rejoin your own
tribe."
(laughs)
Great.
I've got to chew my noodle on
who am I going to give the clue
to the hidden immunity idol to?
This could be a crucial play for
me right here in terms of who I
give this to and how it can come
back to help me later.
Let's see here, what is it you
do, Courtney?
>> No kidding, man!
I love that place!
You make me miss New York so
much!
I want to go back.
>> Dave is a nutcase.
>> I can give you... I can give
you a little plumbers butt if
you want.
Excuse me.
>> It's annoying as hell, but
I'm going to do my best to be
nice to him right now so he can
get a good impression of our
camp.
>> 16 years old.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> I think Todd's a real cool
guy.
He wants to play the game, and
I've got a pretty good hunch.
For whatever it's worth, I
believe I can trust him.
>> I do.
>> That's pretty good.
Let's sit down right here.
Here you go, bro.
Read it and hide it somewhere
up in the grass or something
like that.
>> Deal.
>> Thank you, man.
>> Sweet.
>> Appreciate it.
>> Cool, man.
>> I trust Todd because I asked
a key question of him-- "Do you
believe turnabout's fair
play?"-- because the next one we
win, I can only assume we'll be
kidnapping somebody, and he'll
probably get the same thing.
So we kind of have a little bit
of a loose alliance from tribe
to tribe going on.
>> I feel very lucky right now
that Leslie not only gave me the
clue to the first one, but Dave
gave me the next two.
So I've been keeping my eyes
open, looking for something
that could be the hidden
immunity idol, because that
could be the ticket to a
million dollars.
>> You ready?
>> Yeah.
>> Want me to carry it?
>> Kissing all the girls.
>> I wonder how the other tribe
is starting to feel about him.
I was very happy they took Dave.
Glad to get him out of my hair
for a couple of days.
We haven't had any of that
conflict going on, so my mood
today is actually a lot more
relaxed.
It's nice not to have him
around.
>> We need to boil water for
drinking first.
>> You guys want to do quick
firewood gathering.
>> Dave was really just a
workhorse, as far as whatever
needed to be done that nobody
else wanted to do.
And that really helped us.
And now we're going to have to
pick up that slack.
>> Without Dave, we're
scrounging around, trying to
get everything done.
I don't know, I'm getting
frustrated because I'm just
tired and I feel like some
people are trying to get away
with not helping out.
>> Sweet!
>> Frosti got it!
>> Nice!
>> Everybody has been running
around sweating, trying to do
10 million projects, and I feel
like why even waste energy on
something that is going to just
drain you.
I'm trying to conserve my
energy for the challenges.
So if they want to keep
working, that's okay with me.
I'm going to ride the workhorse
until the tails fall off,
because I'm not doing anything
until I have to.
>> Fishing boats!
>> They're coming, you guys!
>> Hi!
>> Oh!
Our reward today, we had a
fisherman family come with their
boat, and they are going to cook
us a meal, and also teach some
of us how to fish.
>> They said a family.
>> This is the best reward that
we've ever had.
The fisherman came, the family
came.
I am so grateful for them to be
here today.
Their children are so pretty.
Everybody is so nice.
>> Peppers!
>> We've got eggs!
>> Catfish!
>> They came with huge fish,
vegetables.
They came with oils and spices.
>> Oh, my God!
I never thought I would miss
vegetables so much in my life,
but they look absolutely
terrific.
>> When I was a little kid, I
spent a few years in Taiwan,
and I learned some Mandarin
over there.
>> They can only take two out.
>> Jean-Robert is full of
surprises.
He goes off and starts talking
to these people, and it was
fantastic because they were
able to communicate with each
other, and he knew what they
wanted.
>> Aaron, he's going to tell
you guys what to do.
>> It's been 20 years since
I've used Mandarin, but
honestly, when that family
came, all of a sudden, just
words and everything started
coming back to me.
I didn't even know I still had
it.
>> Denise and I went off in the
fisherman's boat, and it was
absolutely the most bizarre
thing I've ever seen.
Oh, they're going to go catch
the fish that we're going to
fish with.
And then they can't swallow it.
>> It was incredible!
I thought we were going to eat
the birds when they showed up,
and they had them all tied to
the boat.
But they're fishing birds.
They had them all trained.
They could swoop down, pick up
the fish.
The bird will regurgitate the
fish right out of his mouth in
the bottom of the boat.
And, I mean, he was picking up
pretty good-sized fish out
there.
>> Be careful inside when you're
pulling this out, because there
are teeth that could cut you.
She needs a fire.
Fire.
>> Dude, I'm just saying... I'm
translating what she's saying.
That's not giving orders.
>> Jean-Robert, he got up on
his high horse as he usually
do, kind of got on everybody's
nerves-- really mine.
>> I said she's asking for
a fire.
>> He was just sitting there
being Jean-Robert, but we needed
him.
He was like the language-
barrier guy.
He came through.
I really couldn't fault him.
He did good.
>> The fisherman showed us how
to open the net, and then he
stretched it out across the
lake so when the fish come
they just swim right into the
net.
Before, we didn't even know how
to use the net.
But now we're going to have
fish.
It's going to be great.
>> Ahoy.
>> Hi.
>> Ahoy, matey.
>> Oh, my God!
>> You guys know what "hao chi"
means?
"Hao" is good, and "chi" is eat.
>> I've never been so happy in
my life.
>> Oh, my God, after being out
here all this time, flavor has
never tasted so good.
Oh, my God!
That's spicy!
You know, a lunch lady is not
an expert on food, because you
know what we do?
We take the chicken nuggets out
of the freezer, we put them in
the oven, we give them to the
kids.
There's nothing good about that.
But this stuff here, that was
the delicatest thing that I've
ever put in my mouth.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you so much.
>> This reward was key for us.
It's not only that we get a
meal but it's a cultural
learning experience, and I
really do think that we're
going to be eating better, and
definitely have an advantage in
the challenges to come.
>> Bye-bye!
Bye!
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
So, Dave, time to rejoin Zhan
Hu.
>> Hi, guys.
Good to see you.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First things
first-- immunity coming back.
>> See you soon, buddy.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
Here's how the challenge is
going to play out: for your own
protection, you will each be
dressed in traditional Chinese
armor.
You'll square off in our
gladiator arena.
Behind each tribe, there are
porcelain vases.
You will throw meteor hammers,
attempting to smash the other
tribe's vases while blocking
your opponent's throws with a
bamboo pole.
We'll go in rounds.
First round will be two women on
a team, then two men, then one
man, one woman.
The tribe that breaks the most
vases in those three rounds
wins immunity, safe at least
another day here in China.
Losers go to tribal council
tonight, somebody going home.
Fei Long, you have one more
member.
You're sitting somebody out.
Cannot sit out the same people
in back-to-back challenges.
Courtney sat out the last
challenge.
She'll be participating
in this.
You must sit out one man.
>> It has to be either me or
Todd.
>> PROBST: Who's sitting this
one out?
>> Jean-Robert is going to sit
out.
>> PROBST: Jean-Robert is
sitting out.
All right, we'll get started.
All right, first teams head out.
>> Go Zhan Hu!
>> Fei Long!
(applause)
>> PROBST: First round is going
to be Denise and Courtney for
Fei Long taking on Peih-gee and
Sherea for Zhan Hu.
Put on your helmets.
Let's get started.
Each team will have three
throws per round.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Let's get them, guys.
Watch what they're doing.
>> PROBST: Denise winding up.
Denise launches first.
She's way over the top.
>> Pick up another one!
>> PROBST: Peih-gee swinging.
Peih-gee short.
You've gotta get some oomph on
these.
Sherea winding up now.
She launches one.
Almost knocks it off.
Courtney winds up.
>> Come on, get it, baby!
>> PROBST: She's short.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Denise winding up.
She tosses her last one.
Blocked nicely by Peih-gee.
Peih-gee gives the last one to
Sherea.
>> Come on, Sherea!
>> PROBST: Sherea launches the
last one and scores!
Round one is over.
Zhan Hu scores one.
Zhan Hu leads 1-0.
Next round, two men for each
team.
For Fei Long, it is Todd and
James.
For Zhan Hu, Frosti, Dave.
Zhan Hu leads 1-0.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Go, guys!
>> PROBST: Todd and James
both pick up meteor hammers, as
do Frosti and Dave.
Gonna be a little more velocity
from the guys.
Dave launches and just misses.
Frosti winding up.
He launches and just misses.
>> Come on, guys, do it, do it.
>> PROBST: Todd and James both
launch and both connect!
Two for Fei Long, they lead 2-1.
Frosti winding up, throws
it right at James, who deflects
it.
James winding up.
It's 2-1.
James has the last throw.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: James connects again!
Fei Long leads 3-1.
Next two head out, the
remaining man and the remaining
woman from each tribe.
For Fei Long, it is Amanda and
Aaron.
For Zhan Hu, it's Jaime and
Erik.
>> Go, Zhan Hu!
>> PROBST: Fei Long leads 3-1.
Zhan Hu, you have a lot of
catching up to do.
This is it.
Each side has three shots.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Amanda and Aaron both picking
up meteor hammers.
Jaime swinging hers.
Who is going to shoot first?
Amanda tosses, deflected by
Jaime.
Aaron tosses, deflected by Erik.
Jaime winding up.
Jaime launches and connects
with two!
We are tied, 3-3.
Erik goes low, deflected by
Aaron.
Amanda winds up.
Amanda tosses her last one and
connects!
Fei Long scores again.
Fei Long now leads 4-3.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu has one shot
left.
You have to break two vases to
win.
Jaime did it before.
Can she do it again?
>> Come on, Jaime!
>> PROBST: Jaime launches.
No, Jaime and Erik can't do it.
Fei Long wins immunity!
>> Whoo!
>> Good job, guys.
Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Fei Long,
congratulations.
Immunity once again.
(applause)
Nobody going home from Fei Long.
Zhan Hu, tribal council tonight.
One of the six of you will be
voted out.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
See you at tribal.
>> It was.
It was hard.
>> Maybe we should eat first,
let our food digest.
>> You want to dump that out so
I can get well water for that?
>> Well, I mean, considering
parasites and stuff, I'd like to
use a lot less lake water as
possible.
You know what I mean?
>> Infinitely better just using
straight well water.
In fact, I'll run and get some,
if you want.
>> I don't care.
>> I don't care, either.
>> It feels very strange to be
back here at Zhan Hu.
We lost the immunity challenge
today, and I don't want to go
home.
But there's very strange vibes
going on.
Maybe it was just the day and a
half away from me, or, you
know, my slave-driving ability.
But, I don't know, I'm feeling
very precarious right now.
>> Today, we have to decide who
to vote off.
It's probably going to be
between Sherea and Dave.
It's a tough decision because,
Sherea, she doesn't really help
out as much as the rest of us
do on camp.
On the other hand, Dave's just
really annoying and really hard
to live with.
>> She's like, "I'm so tired.
I'm weak.
I need to save my energy for
challenges" and just kind of
got into that mode.
"Hey, everybody's cool with
me laying around and not doing
much of anything."
>> They all decided to go take
a dip in the lake.
And of course, when voices get
low, you know something's going
on.
I am concerned that me not
doing as much around camp is
affecting everybody else's
opinion.
So, I already know that my name
may be written down tonight.
People just looking at people
around camp, or people looking
at people in challenges.
You know what I'm saying?
You never know what people are
thinking.
>> But we do have to make these
judgments so quick.
>> Everybody pulls their weight
in different ways.
I mean, yeah, I don't do
everything around camp, but I
get to a challenge, I'm going
to bust my ass to make sure we
win.
Everybody busting their butts
the first few days and
everybody else is getting,
like, fatigued.
My body comes first, you know.
>> It's really close toss-up
between Sherea's not working
and Dave's kind of making
everybody crazy.
It's just been back and forth
in my mind.
I think if it were up to me,
you know, if we could get rid
of both of them, it would be
great.
>> PROBST: Sherea, how did the
tribe dynamic change having Dave
gone for a day?
>> We were able to go ahead
and move on and get things going
the same way we would if he was
there.
We had some relaxing time and
some chill time, but we still
kept busy and got things done
when he was gone.
>> PROBST: Frosti, is that a
credit to Dave for establishing
maybe a work ethic that keeps
on even when he's gone?
>> It can definitely be seen as
a credit to Dave's name.
I mean, he got us going on
making sure we had water
boiling at all times.
We got food done, and even
without him there, we
accomplished a lot, so...
>> PROBST: Erik, you were
nodding your head.
>> I like Dave.
And, honestly, there's been
some disagreements, and it
frustrates me seeing other
people not kind of receiving
Dave's leadership.
You know, Dave has great
leadership qualities.
It's just his natural
personality.
>> PROBST: Dave, would it be a
bit of a relief to go back to
camp and not have to lead
tonight?
>> Absolutely.
It's been quite a burden.
It's been something I didn't
want to begin with.
I just happen to have more
experience and more practical
ideas, and that's how we got
where we are today.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about camp
life.
You've been out here 12 days
now.
Sherea, everybody still pulling
their own weight?
>> Definitely, everybody's
doing something.
I'm stepping it up a lot more.
>> PROBST: From what to what?
>> I've been very fatigued, and,
just, my body hasn't been in it
when I'm around, you know, the
camp area, so the last few days,
I've been trying to do more.
But if we don't save our energy
for challenges, we'll never get
further ahead in the game.
>> PROBST: Dave, is camp life
more important than challenge
participation, or should you
sacrifice at camp to make sure
you have a shot at winning?
>> Saving just for challenges
is a short-term goal, because
if you are not fed, if you are
not rested and hydrated, it
will just take its toll.
>> PROBST: Peih-gee, if given
the choice between somebody
pulling their weight back at
camp or being invincible at
challenges?
>> You know, honestly, I know
you want me to pick one, but
you can't.
You need to have a balance
between the two, and if you
don't, it's going to put an
undue burden on the rest of the
tribe.
>> She enjoys camp life.
I live for the challenges.
She loves to be out here in
this environment.
>> I love the challenges, too.
>> I know, but I'm just
saying that's why you can say
both.
She's always like, "Yeah, I
love it out here!
This is easy for me."
And I'm like, "This is not easy
for me," you know.
But the challenges, I live for
those.
That's what keeps me going
every day.
>> PROBST: Once again, you guys
are in a position of trying to
adjust tribe dynamics, and
you're going to do it by
getting rid of somebody.
It is time to vote.
Erik, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Dave.
Sherea.
One vote Dave, one vote Sherea.
Dave.
Two votes Dave, one vote Sherea.
Three votes Dave, one vote
Sherea.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: China, Dave.
That's four, it's enough.
You need to bring me your
torch.
Dave, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> PROBST: Well, it's clear from
tonight's vote that you weren't
happy with the way things were
going at camp.
I hope that means there's a new
plan in place.
Because you're going to need
one.
You're now two members down.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I like you a lot.
>> PROBST: Jaime and Erik
explore new territory.
>> I don't know what's going to
happen with Jaime and I.
I'm a virgin.
>> PROBST: And a twist...
>> Something's going on.
>> PROBST: ...turns the game on
its head.
>> Oh, the humanity.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> I gave it my all, perhaps I
gave it too much.
At least I did it with
conviction and integrity.
I thought I was humble.
And I thought I listened.
I wish that some people
perhaps listened to me a little
bit more.
And I know there are pieces of
me that are worth a lot,
perhaps even priceless, you
know.
If they can't see that, then,
well, I can't force them.