>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
Tenth person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury,
James.
...after the tribe successfully
blindsided James, Peih-Gee
realized that she might have a
shot at winning it all.
>> There must be a crack in old
tribal lines somewhere, because
Erik and I are still around.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
>> What?
>> PROBST: ...a visit from
family brought the tribe to
tears.
>> I love you.
>> Can I have your socks?
>> PROBST: Paired up for the
challenge...
Survivors and loved ones, ready?
Go!
...Denise and her husband found
their way to victory.
Denise and Robert win reward!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: And Denise chose two
former Fei Long members to join
her on the reward...
>> Thank you!
>> PROBST: ...leaving Peih-Gee
feeling betrayed.
>> I wonder why Denise picked
Amanda.
I'm kind of pissed that she
didn't pick me, because I took
her on a phat reward.
>> PROBST: During the reward,
Denise felt that she
strengthened her bond with Todd
and Amanda.
>> I hope that Amanda and Todd
stay with me and we go to the
final three.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
Go!
...Peih-Gee dug out a come-from-
behind victory.
Peih-Gee wins immunity!
...establishing herself as a
force to be reckoned with.
Guaranteed a spot in the final
five.
With Peih-Gee safe, Erik was on
the chopping block, but Erik and
Peih-Gee came up with a plan to
turn the game around.
>> I'm voting for Todd.
It might be a long shot, but...
>> I'll talk to Denise.
>> PROBST: They tried to
convince Denise to join them and
vote out the mastermind.
>> I'm definitely the swing vote
tonight.
For me, personally, I mean, this
is do or die.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Denise stayed true to her
alliance of Todd, Amanda, and
Courtney.
11th person voted out and the
fifth member of our jury.
Erik was voted out, leaving
Peih-Gee the only remaining Zhan
Hu member.
Five are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Congratulations, final five!
>> Peih-Gee and Erik approached
me earlier, and they wanted me
to vote out Todd tonight.
Here I could have been at least
in the top three and tried to
make it at least to the jury
vote.
But I kind of decided to play it
safe, even though this could
have been one of the biggest
mistakes I've made in the game
so far.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> I'm probably not the most
popular one here, as you can
see.
You have the four original Fei
Long members, and they've really
been sticking together.
It's not easy feeling like
you're the least liked, so I'm
definitely, like, an outsider,
you know, and it's hard.
Oh, my God.
You guys, rise and shine.
We have tree mail.
>> Arrows, huh?
>> "Ready, aim, take your best
shot.
Get by with a little help from
your friends.
Are you skilled or just popular?
In this challenge, it all
depends.
The next reward is within your
sights.
This one will blow your mind.
As far as incredible experiences
go, this is one of a kind."
>> Rewards right now are key.
They help you stay alive.
They help you push for the next
day.
They make you smile.
So I'm really, really hoping I'm
skilled and popular right now.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
reward challenge?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will each fire
arrows from a replica of a
fourth-century Chinese repeating
crossbow.
Each time you or anyone else
hits your name on the target
wall, you'll score a point.
You'll each begin with five
arrows.
But to make it interesting,
you'll come behind this wall and
secretly distribute your arrows
to the other survivors by
placing them in marked
containers.
Each time you give someone else
an arrow, you give them another
shot at the wall, a better
chance of winning the game.
At the end of the challenge, the
person whose name has been hit
the most often wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Uh-huh.
>> PROBST: The winner will be
flown via private jet to one of
the most spectacular manmade
wonders in the entire world, the
Great Wall of China.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: You'll enjoy a
wonderful meal on the Great
Wall, and you will spend the
night at the Great Wall.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Uh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Let's get to the
challenge.
First step, give away your
arrows.
Amanda, come back here.
You'll find five vases.
Put the arrows in any container
you wish other than your own.
You can give all your arrows to
one person.
You can divide them up equally,
however you want.
You cannot put them in your own
container.
Okay, everybody has distributed
their arrows.
Let's see the results.
Peih-Gee, you have your
container in front of you.
Remove your arrows.
>> Thank you, Courtney.
>> PROBST: One arrow.
Todd gets a total of six arrows.
Denise.
>> Two.
>> PROBST: Denise with only two
arrows.
>> You know, I'm the bottom of
the totem pole.
>> PROBST: Courtney.
>> I have many arrows.
>> PROBST: Courtney with 12
arrows.
You have the most chances to win
thus far.
Amanda.
Amanda with a total of four
arrows.
The person with the least amount
of arrows will shoot first.
That'll be you, Peih-Gee.
You're up.
One arrow courtesy of Courtney.
Let's see if you can get on the
board.
Peih-Gee misses just high.
Denise, you're next up with two
arrows.
Denise trying to hit her own
name and not somebody else's.
Denise misses high.
>> It's okay, Denise.
Focus.
>> PROBST: Denise with only one
more shot.
Look at that.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Denise nails it.
>> Very impressive.
>> PROBST: Denise on the board
with one.
Next up is Amanda, four arrows.
Amanda misses low.
>> Get the green one.
>> PROBST: Denise gets hit.
>> Yes!
>> It did hit the green one.
>> PROBST: Denise now in the
lead with two.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Denise sitting
pretty, not doing anything.
Amanda misses high.
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Todd, you're up.
Todd has six arrows to shoot.
Todd, nice job.
Todd hits his own name.
Todd on the board with one.
Todd!
>> There you go, Todd, nice one.
>> Nice job.
>> PROBST: Todd scores again
with two.
Todd has not missed yet.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: And he's hit a
different target each time.
Todd and Denise now tied with
three.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: As if he'd shot the
Chinese repeating crossbow his
entire life.
>> Secretly a hobby of mine.
>> PROBST: Todd now leads 4-3.
Wow.
>> There you go.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Todd cannot miss.
Todd is five for five.
Todd leads 5-3.
Todd finally misses on his sixth
shot.
Nice demonstration!
Todd in the lead, five.
Denise in second with three.
Courtney, it's all in your
hands.
>> Come on, Courtney.
>> PROBST: Courtney with 12
arrows, the most of anybody.
Courtney misses high and to the
right.
>> That's all right.
You got plenty of arrows.
>> PROBST: Courtney connects.
>> Yeah!
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Courtney now on the
board with one.
Courtney hits Denise, giving
Denise another point.
It is now Todd with five, Denise
with four, Courtney with one.
>> Ooh, Amanda.
>> PROBST: Courtney scores one
for Amanda.
>> This is, like, anyone's game
at this point.
>> PROBST: Just misses Denise.
Courtney hits Todd's target.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Todd's lead is now
six to Denise's four.
Courtney hits another Denise
target, keeping it tight now.
Another Denise hit by Courtney.
We are tied now, Denise with
six, Todd with six.
Todd gets the hit.
>> Thank you, baby doll.
>> No problem, babykins.
>> PROBST: Todd leads 7-6.
Oh, just misses a Todd.
>> Baby, please!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Courtney hits another
Denise target.
We are tied 7-7 between Todd and
Denise.
Courtney with only one arrow
left.
What is she going to do?
>> Go for the green.
Go for the green.
Right over there, it says
"Denise."
Yes!
>> PROBST: Denise wins reward!
( applause )
>> Congratulations.
>> PROBST: Denise, come on over.
Private jet.
>> So exciting.
>> PROBST: Nice meal, spend the
night on the Great Wall.
Pick one person to come with
you.
>> Courtney.
>> Yay.
>> You got me here.
>> Have fun.
>> PROBST: Denise, we could let
you two go alone, but that's not
what's happening.
>> Oh, Denise, please!
>> PROBST: Denise, you're going
to pick one more person to go
with you.
>> I'm going to be on the jury,
girl.
I took you.
I gave you Shaolin monks.
I gave you food when I knew you
were sick.
>> PROBST: All right, Denise,
you're taking one, which means
two people will not go on this
reward.
Who is the second person coming
with you?
>> I'm going to have to pick
Todd.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Todd, come on over.
Wow, Peih-Gee, you look
absolutely disappointed.
>> I took Denise on a great
reward.
I gave her Shaolin monks.
I took her because I knew she
was sick, and, like, I've been
friendly to her from the very
beginning, and she just doesn't
care.
You know, and I've eaten the
least out of everybody.
I've had to fight the hardest.
And it's just... it's tough.
I'm being left out of
everything, so...
>> PROBST: Amanda, how you
feeling?
>> Yeah, it's not a good
feeling, you know, but, I mean,
what can do you?
>> PROBST: Not much, because I
got nothing for you.
>> I'm sorry, guys.
>> PROBST: Denise, Todd,
Courtney, you will fly to the
Great Wall of China, have a nice
meal, spend the night.
Great reward, enjoy it, get your
stuff, head out.
>> Just me and you.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm pissed.
After the challenge, I
definitely lost my cool, you
know, said some things that I
probably shouldn't have.
It's just frustrating.
I mean, I picked Denise for a
reward, and to have her win
twice now and not pick me, it's
tough.
And then also I heard her say,
"I don't want Peih-Gee getting
any stronger."
That part makes me mad, because
it's like, hello, I'm still a
person.
>> Everything is so much work,
as it is, and then, like, having
to do it all just sucks.
Don't screw this up, Amanda.
It's coming down to, like, the
end of the game, and three
people are having meals and
eating, and I used to be one of
those three, and now I'm not.
So it's... it's hard.
Why is it you dislike me so
much?
>> Huh?
>> Why do you dislike me so
much?
>> I don't dislike you, Amanda,
seriously.
>> Because it's like ever since
you came here, like, you haven't
really talked to me at all, and,
like, at tribal, I feel like
you're always attacking me.
>> I mean, I'm sorry.
Like, honestly, like, I'm sorry
that, like... if it hurts your
feelings or anything like that.
It's really...
>> No, I just want to know,
because I'd like to get it...
I'd like to get it out, like...
>> Yeah, no, actually, I'm glad
that, like, we get some time to
spend together, because, like...
>> I am, too, actually.
>> Like, I, like... we really
haven't had a lot of time to
talk, and, like, I think it's
cool that we get to... you know,
get to know each other a little
better.
>> Yeah, me, too.
>> I actually respect Amanda for
speaking her mind.
I think we had some just
miscommunication with her making
assumptions of me and me making
assumptions of her, and it's
because we hadn't had a chance
to really sit down and talk.
>> There's one.
>> Awesome.
>> Right there.
There's one.
>> Ooh, that was a huge one.
>> I know.
>> Awesome.
>> Yay, we have food.
Oh, we just found a huge Asian
pear and huge limes, so we're
really happy, because we have
food to eat.
Yay!
Life doesn't suck right now.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> You guys are awesome.
>> How cool is this?
I'm so grateful you picked me.
Peih-Gee we can't feed right now
because...
>> No, I can't give her
anything.
And I feel bad.
She was like, "I'm not going to
vote for you now," and being all
pissed off.
You know, what am I supposed to
do?
>> The thing is, though, is
Amanda, she understands that in
the game, she's in a good spot
with us.
Plus, what is she going to do,
align with Peih-Gee and a bush
right now?
You know what I mean?
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome on
board Survivor Airlines, flight
number 15, the three coolest
people going to the Great Wall
of China.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> Thanks, Denise!
>> Thanks, Todd.
>> Oh, wow, look.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Oh-wee.
It just keeps going.
>> To win the challenge and
actually go to the Great Wall of
China was an incredible thing.
The views stretch off all the
way on the hills and the
mountains.
And then we actually got up
there-- I mean, just amazing to
be standing someplace where 600
years ago there were soldiers
running back and forth and
cannons.
And, you know, just to be
staying in the same place was
amazing.
>> Thank you.
>> And our beds are right here
too.
>> Thank you.
>> Is it fondue?
>> It smells good.
>> You dip it in.
>> I'm confused.
>> I'm super confused.
>> We had this huge table full
of food, and we all kind of
looked at it like, "What are we
supposed to do with it?
It's all raw."
And there was a big bowl thing
in front of us.
I guess we put it in here.
This little Chinese waiter guy
comes in, and he starts saying,
"Dip it and put it in..."
And we're like, "Okay."
>> Yeah, exactly.
That's sweet.
That's good.
>> Mm.
>> It turned into a big
jambalaya pot of, like, stuff,
and I was surprised at how quick
I got full.
It was like that that my body
was like, "You're done."
At least Peih-Gee will hopefully
be weak.
>> She will also be filled with
hatred that will spur her to
action.
>> Exactly.
>> It was sort of a strategic
thing to have Denise bring Todd
instead of Amanda to this,
because Amanda is a lot less
likely to stir up trouble back
at camp than Todd would be.
An angry Todd is a bad Todd.
>> Do you see how many there
are?
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
We strung out the net yesterday,
and we didn't know if we were
going to catch anything because
we've had nothing in our nets
for, like, a week.
So we start pulling up the net,
me and Peih-Gee, and there's,
like, tons of fish.
It feels fabulous.
>> Delightful seafood risotto
with a little red wine reduction
and rice wine.
Pour it in, girl.
Oops.
>> Oops, I used it all the sake.
Oh, my God!
>> Is it delicious?
>> Uh-huh.
This is good.
>> It's totally good.
>> Oh, my God.
>> There's, like, seriously,
like, enough rice for, like, two
days though.
>> Up until this point, I had
nothing on Amanda, and I have a
lot more insight on her, and
I've actually gotten more
information on the dynamics of
their old group.
>> I am open for things.
I have been the whole time.
>> That's too funny that, like,
we've been on, like, the same
wavelength.
>> I know.
>> At this point in the game, it
looks maybe she really isn't
dead set on going with Todd and
Courtney yet.
It gives me a little bit of
hope.
>> Ooh, what's this?
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God, thank you!
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> It's so good!
>> I'm the happiest boy alive
right now.
I just want to bring up a
question, like, and I don't know
how to think about it, but,
like, say Peih-Gee did win
immunity again.
>> Oh, lord.
>> Would we want a fight between
the four of us, or would we want
to take off our love, Amanda?
>> I don't know.
What do you want to do?
>> I think all of us are going
to say, "I don't want to go
home."
But I think, you know, people's
answers would probably change if
she was sitting here.
>> I mean, I know I'm tight with
Amanda.
I have been for a long time.
But I'm trying to think, too,
like, can we beat her?
>> Do we beat her?
>> We're the meanies!
I mean, good lord, me and Todd
are like the devil incarnate in
this game.
They hate us.
>> In this four person alliance,
I kind of feel scared, because
Todd's backstabbed a lot of
people.
He's been making alliances with
everybody and not telling
anybody and doing shifty things.
>> We know we're catty.
We might as well just go to the
end together, right?
>> Yes.
>> This is a critical time right
now.
Someone is going to be left out
of our group, and I don't want
it to be me.
>> Is anybody home?
Where are they?
>> When we got back to camp,
Peih-Gee and Amanda weren't
there, and we were like, "Um,
where are you guys?
Like, where did everybody go?"
And I was concerned because they
were pissed when we left.
>> Are we getting extreme
Survivor paranoia right now?
>> Oh, yeah, look.
>> Hi, girls!
>> Hi!
>> Hey, guys!
>> Yeah.
>> Amazing, huh?
>> The Great Wall was so neat.
>> But it's a cultural
experience.
>> It was a big, huge table, and
there was sliced chicken and
sliced pork...
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Raw.
>> ...that was raw that we had
to put in the soup to eat.
There was a dipping sauce.
>> Which made all of us, like,
upset stomachs.
>> It made our stomachs go
weird.
We had to dip it, like, oil.
We didn't know what to do.
>> We had no idea.
>> They come back from the Great
Wall, and they were complaining.
The food, nobody explained to
them how to eat it, and they
didn't like the food.
It's like, "Come on!"
>> Hey, at least you got to eat,
though.
>> That's true.
>> Todd and Courtney still find
things to complain about when
they win a reward?
It just blows my mind.
Some people are so ungrateful,
and honestly, it made me mad.
>> I'm kind of upset with Todd
and Courtney.
They didn't bring anything back
for me and Peih-Gee.
They know I haven't eaten very
much.
So Denise is showing a little
more compassion to my situation
than Todd, and it's definitely
going noticed.
>> Absolutely.
>> Okay, that sounds good.
>> All right.
Hm.
You ready?
"What doesn't kill you makes you
stronger.
This time it means much more.
A second chance to prove
yourself may get you to the
final four."
It's a repeat of previous
challenges mixed together.
>> Yeah.
>> Peih-Gee is probably most
under the gun today to win
immunity, but so is Todd.
I don't trust a thing he says.
If he can backstab everyone in
this game to get himself an inch
further, he would.
So if he doesn't win next
immunity challenge, I may have
to think about getting rid of
Todd.
>> PROBST: Guys ready to get to
today's immunity challenge?
First things first.
Peih-Gee, take it back.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
get a chance to revisit some of
the challenges from the past 36
days.
It will take place in four
rounds.
For the first round, each of you
will throw three stars at a
target.
The four highest scorers move on
to the next round, where you
must eat one balut.
The first three to get the balut
down move on to the next round,
where you must bounce a ball on
a drum through a series of
obstacles and into a finish bin.
The first two to finish move on
to the final round.
For the final round, you will
use a sword to release wooden
disks.
>> Oh, no!
>> PROBST: You'll use the disks
to complete a puzzle.
First one to finish wins
immunity, is guaranteed a spot
in the final four.
Losers, tribal council tonight,
somebody will be going home.
We'll draw for spots, and we'll
get started.
All right, first round.
Peih-Gee, you're up first.
Three stars, trying to score as
many points as you can.
Peih-Gee connects on her first
toss.
Two points Peih-Gee.
Peih-Gee short.
Peih-Gee misses again.
Peih-Gee scores two.
Denise, you're up.
You need two or more.
Denise short and low.
You need to get on that board.
That'll work.
Denise with a three.
And another three.
Denise with six points.
Peih-Gee with two points.
Amanda's up.
Amanda's short.
Not strong enough on that one.
One shot left for Amanda, and
she connects with a three.
Amanda on the board with three.
Denise with six.
Peih-Gee with two.
Courtney's up next.
Courtney with a nice shot.
Courtney on the board with two.
Just misses the three.
Courtney low.
Courtney scores two.
She's tied at the bottom with
Peih-Gee.
Four highest scorers move on.
Todd has to score two or more to
stay in this.
Todd scores one on his first
throw.
Oh, it sticks in the one and
falls out.
Todd one throw left.
You have one point.
You need at least one point on
this throw.
Todd doesn't get it.
Todd does not move on.
Everybody else moving on to the
next round.
Here we go, first three to get
the balut down move on to the
next round.
Survivors ready?
Three, two, one, eat.
Denise is the only one who tried
this, and she could not get it
down.
Peih-Gee eating quickly.
Courtney shoves half of it in
her mouth.
Do not think about what you're
eating.
Think about something else and
shove it down.
Peih-Gee, you don't see any
problem with this, do you?
>> It's so good.
>> Good, Courtney.
Chew it, chew it, chew it.
Hurry up.
>> PROBST: Denise, are you just
out?
>> Yeah.
I can't.
I tried.
>> PROBST: Yeah.
>> Chew, chew, chew, chew.
>> PROBST: Amanda's good.
She's moving on.
Peih-Gee's good.
There's one spot left.
It is between Courtney and
Denise.
Denise, after 36 days and a one-
in-four shot, you're not even
trying.
>> I put it in my mouth, and I
puked it up again, Jeff.
I really wish I could.
>> PROBST: A million-dollar
balut in front of you.
It is Courtney moving on.
Denise take a spot on the bench.
We're moving up.
All right, for this round, you
must bounce the ball on the
drum, over a series of
obstacles.
First two to bounce a ball into
their finish bin move on to the
final round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Got to keep the ball bouncing,
cannot carry it.
Peih-Gee past the first
obstacle, into the second
section.
Peih-Gee loses it, got to head
back to the start.
Courtney, got to go back to the
start.
Amanda now into the second
section.
>> You're doing great.
>> Take your time, Courtney.
>> PROBST: Amanda very close to
being into the final section.
Got to get over the bamboo.
And she does.
Amanda very close.
Amanda is in the bin.
Amanda's moving on.
One more person moving on.
Peih-Gee keeping it alive.
Courtney keeping it alive.
Peih-Gee into the final section.
Peih-Gee moving on!
Amanda and Peih-Gee in the
final!
All right, the final round.
You must use your sword,
chopping through rope to release
eight wooden disks.
You must then use the disks to
complete a puzzle.
First person to get it right,
guaranteed spot in the final
four.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
Amanda not messing around at
all, now working on her second
rope.
Peih-Gee's through the first
Peih-Gee working on the second
rope.
Amanda has two ropes chopped.
Peih-Gee chops through her
second rope.
They're both on the third rope.
Amanda working it.
One rope left for Amanda.
Peih-Gee through her third rope.
Amanda's through all four ropes,
moving the disks up.
Peih-Gee's now through all four
ropes.
She's moving on to the puzzle
stage.
Got to get all your disks back
to the platform before you can
begin.
>> Line them all up.
Yeah, yeah, go!
>> PROBST: Amanda getting some
encouragement from Denise.
Peih-Gee getting no love.
First person to solve this
puzzle is going to the final
four.
Loser going to tribal council,
one in four shot at being voted
out.
Amanda has two pieces complete
on the puzzle.
Peih-Gee still working on her
first.
Amanda working on that third
piece.
Does she have the right one?
She does.
Amanda with three pieces
completed.
Peih-Gee completes her first
piece.
There are eight pieces total to
this puzzle.
Peih-Gee with her second piece.
Got to catch up!
Amanda has four pieces.
She's halfway finished.
Peih-Gee with her third piece.
Amanda with her fifth piece.
Only three left.
Amanda not sure if she has the
right piece or not.
Puzzle only goes together one
way.
Peih-Gee with her fourth piece.
Amanda giving Peih-Gee a chance
to get back in this.
Amanda has her sixth piece.
Amanda down to two pieces left.
Peih-Gee with her fifth piece.
Amanda with her seventh piece.
This is it.
Amanda wins immunity, going to
the final four!
>> I won immunity, you guys!
>> Good job.
>> I never thought...
>> PROBST: Amanda, come on over.
You are guaranteed a spot in the
final four-- not going anywhere.
Peih-Gee, Todd, Courtney,
Denise, after 36 days, somebody
going home tonight.
See you at tribal.
Grab your stuff.
Head on back to camp.
>> Thank you.
>> Oh, my God.
That was tough.
I came so close to winning
immunity again.
So it's just a sharp
disappointment, because I'm next
on the chopping block almost for
sure.
But I think there's a chance
that I can turn this around for
me, and I think Amanda is my
best hope right now for a
reprieve.
>> You did such a great job,
kid.
>> Thank you.
>> I'm so proud of you.
>> Thanks.
I was really excited to win
immunity today because I just
wanted a for-sure final four
spot.
And so I'm stoked.
And this is kind of a neat thing
for me because I have a little
bit of power right now, having
the immunity.
>> That's it?
>> That's it.
>> You guys went to town
yesterday, didn't you?
We had more than that.
>> Todd made this comment, "Oh,
my God, you guys ate so much
rice.
We have no rice left."
And I just kind of looked at him
like, "I don't even want to hear
it."
It took everything I had not to,
like, flip out.
>> Exactly.
>> And we have to both watch
each other's back.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
I agree with that.
>> I have been dancing around
the idea of getting rid of Todd
for a while now, because he's a
threat.
He's a strategist, you know?
Like, he could go behind my back
at any point in this game and
take me out.
Me and Peih-Gee have definitely
bonded on a personal level, so
I'm beginning to think maybe
I'll have a better chance to get
in the final three right now
with Denise and Peih-Gee.
>> I fought so hard to be here,
and I've played, like, what I
think is, like, a pretty, like,
honorable game.
>> I know you have.
>> And, like, Todd has been
backstabbing people and lying to
people and playing everybody,
like, left and right.
>> Peih-Gee is on the outsides
right now, and everybody's
trying to vote her off.
So she's trying to get rid of
Todd, and I don't blame her.
But Todd's made a lot of enemies
on the jury, and I think I have
a chance of winning against Todd
if I keep him in the finals.
So I'm still torn.
>> I like you so much.
Like, our day together changed
my whole view of you, and I
don't want to vote you out.
>> I don't either.
>> I hope you guys knock off
Todd.
It'd be, like, three girls.
I mean, I don't know what you
guys are planning, but I'd like
to see that happen.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh-uh.
>> I think she's probably at
that stage where she realizes
that she doesn't have any hope.
Yeah.
Yeah, watch me get blindsided
tonight.
I had a little bit of paranoia
when I saw my name read twice at
the last tribal council, but I
still feel kind of comfortable.
It's just really, really, really
worked out for me that my
alliance was the right one.
Peih-Gee was coming off as a
fighter, and that's why she has
to go so badly.
If she somehow convinces those
other girls to vote me off, I
will be pissed off if I go
home-- like, livid.
But big ups to them for figuring
a way to get rid of me.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury: Jaime,
Jean-Robert, Frosti, James, and
Erik, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Denise, let's talk about winning
the reward challenge.
You get to bring two people with
you and, on the other hand,
leave two people behind.
>> Definitely a dilemma.
I mean, what a tough decision.
I... you know, I was turmoil in
my brain.
I knew I had to pick Courtney.
She hasn't been eating.
She hasn't gone on a lot of the
challenges.
And I picked Todd to go with me
as well.
>> PROBST: Courtney, tell me
about the reward.
>> Um, the food proved to be a
little confusing for the three
of us.
Like, you know, I consider
myself a pretty adventurous
eater, but you know, when your
body wants things that it
recognizes, it's kind of
frustrating.
So it would have been nice to be
like, "Pizza and beer, whoo!"
You know, like, "Yay, party!"
But I'm negative Nancy, so
that's just... that's me.
I would have wanted pizza.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, what's up?
You're shaking your head.
>> It's just... for me, it just
gets really frustrating, because
I am one of those positive
people, and I've been fighting
hard every day, and to hear
somebody say, "Well, I kind of
tend to be negative about
things, and I kind of haven't
really cared about the game, I'm
only here because other people
have let me stay in it," it's
just really frustrating, and it
hurts me.
Like, it does.
>> PROBST: Amanda, this is
really the first chance you've
had to bond with Peih-Gee.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Did it give you a
different perspective on her?
>> Oh, it definitely did.
I got to learn a lot about Peih-
Gee, and I really respect, like,
how she's made it this far, and
she's still strong and fighting,
and I really respect her for
that.
So it was nice.
>> PROBST: Courtney, does it
matter to you if somebody's
deserving or not, or are you
playing strictly to be with
people that you can beat?
>> How can you look at anyone
who sat outside for 36 days and
put up with all this insanity
and say you don't deserve to be
here?
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, after
tonight's vote, will the four
people left be the four most
deserving?
>> For me, most deserving means
somebody who fought hard every
single chance they had, you
know, really came out here and
challenged themselves.
I think somebody who managed to
get to this same position and
did it honorably, I think they
deserve it more than somebody
who got to the same position and
did it by cheating, lying,
backstabbing, all of that.
>> PROBST: Todd, where do you
stand on that?
If you could take somebody that
was a shoe-in you would beat or
another person who might be a
tougher competitor but
definitely deserved that chance
at a million dollars, which way
would you go?
>> Honestly, I think I've pissed
the most people off, and that's
kind of key.
I don't know how many of them
won't vote for me just because
they actually hate my guts.
So when it's a million dollars
on the line, you got to look at
yourself and say, "Who am I
going to beat, you know, in the
finals?"-- not "Who played a
fantastic game that can probably
kick my ass?"
>> PROBST: All right, Amanda,
you have immunity.
You always have the option to
give it to somebody else.
>> I'll keep it.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Amanda.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Todd, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Peih-Gee.
Todd.
One vote Peih-Gee, one vote
Peih-Gee.
Two votes Peih-Gee, one vote
Todd.
12th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury, Peih-
Gee.
That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, the tribe
has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, you have only three days
left, but still a lot to contend
with-- challenges, strategy, and
ultimately, the jury.
Should make for a fun finish.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> If anyone would backstab me
right now, you would.
>> PROBST: ...will Amanda
blindside Todd?
>> Paranoia on my side is quite
high.
>> PROBST: Who will be the first
to turn on the other?
>> I just don't want to go home
yet.
>> PROBST: Join us for the two-
hour season finale and find out
who will be the sole survivor.
>> I'm glad that I played to my
utmost.
I pushed myself physically,
mentally, strategically, and
ultimately, everybody was scared
to death to go against me in
final three.
So I'm not going to be a
millionaire, but I still feel
like I walked away way richer
than I was before I came into
this game.