>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor ...
At Fei Long, Jean-Robert slept
while everyone else worked.
>> Jean-Robert, you need to
start pulling your weight.
He's a liability for the group.
>> PROBST: And Leslie began a
downward spiral.
>> The last few days, I have
been really sick.
If I can spend some time with
God, it would be great.
>> PROBST: But at the reward
challenge, Fei Long remained
undefeated.
Fei Long wins!
At the challenge, a twist was
revealed.
Fei Long, because you defeated
Zhan Hu, you now get to kidnap
one member of their tribe.
Who are you going to kidnap?
>> Jaime.
>> PROBST: Jaime, this is for
you.
It says, "open in private."
Inside the bamboo tube was a
clue to the hidden immunity
idol.
>> "You must give this sealed
clue to a member of this tribe
before you rejoin your own
tribe."
>> PROBST: And Jaime gave the
clue to Leslie, lifting her
spirits.
>> I feel like the Lord, He
really gave me a gift.
>> PROBST: At Zhan Hu, Dave
used all his energy working
around camp.
And at the immunity challenge...
>> Pick it up, Dave!
>> PROBST: ...he had nothing
left...
Dave is worn out.
...helping Fei Long win their
third challenge in a row.
Fei Long wins immunity!
When Zhan Hu returned to camp,
Dave knew he was in the hot
seat.
>> I apologize.
I feel like I let us down today.
>> Start the fire...
>> Let me finish.
>> The fire...
>> PROBST: But his constant
bickering with Ashley...
>> You're the leader, and I'll
let you do what you want.
>> How many fires have you
built, sweetheart?
...put them both in jeopardy.
At tribal council, the Zhan Hu
tribe decided to give their
hardest worker another chance...
The second person voted out of
the Survivor: China...
...and got rid of Ashley.
Ashley, the tribe has spoken.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(snoring)
>> Oh, gosh.
>> Eww!
Just, please don't.
>> Jean-Robert, God love him, he
like, takes up the whole bed,
and he's, like, hugging on all
the women and we're just like,
"Eww, just please don't."
I don't know what it is about
him.
Maybe it's the silk shirt and
the no underwear.
That did it for me.
>> I need to be warm.
>> Look, will you stop
snuggling so much because
you're scaring the girls.
(laughter)
>> I do get kind of a creep
vibe from Jean-Robert and so
does Amanda.
Neither one of us likes him.
I'm sure he's noticed she and I
will both go to great pains to
not be next to him in the
shelter, and yet he will just
climb in there, and he's like,
"I need Amanda and Courtney by
my side.
They keep me warm."
Like I'm going to keep anyone
warm.
I weigh seven pounds.
I can't even keep myself warm.
Get off of me.
>> Call me creepy, if you want
to, but I need to be warm.
>> I don't think Jean-Robert
gets the social game of
Survivor.
If we ever have to go to tribal
council, at least we don't have
to worry about who it'll be
first because it'll be him.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS and PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> Are we going to eat the
crab?
>> Yeah, we're going to be
eating the crab.
Are you kidding me?
We're going to be eating the
crab.
>> Make a stew.
Crab stew.
>> That looks like a big crab,
man.
>> Are you guys going to cook
the crab?
I think you should boil it
because then it will be like
crab stock and you can put rice
in it and it will be like a
whole meal.
>> You're not going to taste
crabby rice from a crab that
big.
>> It's better than the rice
with nothing we've been eating.
>> The stock.
It's about stretching with eight
people.
>> Stretching the crab?
There's eight of us and one
crab.
>> Okay, okay, so there's only
so much flavor in one crab.
>> So, fine, James caught the
crab so he gets to eat it and
the rest of us have plain rice.
>> We don't work like that.
It's not like you grab kindling
and nobody gets to sit around
the fire.
>> The boys are just cranky.
I know from experience, my
husband, when he gets hungry,
gets really cranky, so I make
sure that man is fed, okay?
And these guys are not getting
fed, so it's like my husband
times infinity.
>> I understand that.
>> Nice crunchy and crispy right
in my mouth.
>> We only have one, so next
time...
>> I know.
I'm just saying this is what I
would like.
>> But I want the damn crab
stock to put on the damn rice.
>> Crab stock on the rice
sounds good.
>> Yeah, besides half a damn
crab.
Which you ain't even gonna get
a half a crab; you'll get a crab
toenail.
>> That's cool.
I'm down with you caught it and
let's do what you want to do.
>> All right, I'm with that,
too.
>> Damn.
>> It's frustrating with this
team because they have a slow
learning curve.
But it's hard to talk to these
guys.
They keep bumping their heads.
I'm the only one that actually
went to Barnes & Noble before
we got out here.
I'm the only one that actually
went and read a survival
handbook.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> I don't eat outside.
I don't even like plastic or
paper cups.
I mean, I don't do nothing
outside.
Four hours at Barnes & Noble
and I know more than... I feel
like Crocodile Dundee out here.
>> Dave, why don't you sit and
eat?
>> I will.
>> I just want you to conserve
your energy because I do not
want to lose another challenge.
Dave doesn't seem to learn.
He knew that last challenge was
him just burning out of energy.
And he doesn't seem to get it
that he needs to rest.
>> No, I'll do the first one.
Someone can do the next one.
Peih-gee.
(kissing sound)
Peih-gee, I've heard you, thank
you, I'm checking myself
constantly.
Please.
Cut me a wee bit of slack, you
know what I mean?
Peih-gee is just riding my butt
about not getting enough rest.
In order to save your energy
and to have energy for a
challenge, you must efficiently
expend some.
It is a balance.
Camp doesn't sort itself out.
If you don't sort out camp,
challenges will tank.
It's not rocket science.
>> We need to take better care
of our stuff.
>> Just stick the wok through
it.
>> Maybe if we had two sticks it
wouldn't tip.
>> Okay, look at me.
You've got a brick in the back
and two bricks in the side.
The fire's right here, right?
>> Yeah, but the fire is
smoldering out towards the
front.
It's not really in between the
bricks.
>> Yeah, I don't know why
you're getting a brick.
We already have one.
>> Well, we've got an extra one
just in case.
I can hem and haw and waffle
about it all day long or just
put a brick on it and go.
This is my whinge for the
moment, and that's me and I'm
done.
So if you take offense, I
apologize, but in the amount of
time it took me to get up, grab
a brick and just do it versus
the time it took to question
it, it just took so much more
time and effort.
>> The only thing that we were
saying is that if you just,
like, sat there for, like, two
more seconds, they already
had the brick right there.
>> Well, forgive me, I'm...
>> Erik, can you hand me some of
that branch?
>> Yeah, Dave's pushing a whole
lot of people and he needs to
chill out.
We were looking at him and
Ashley last night, and today of
all days should be the day when
he should just be happy that
he's here.
>> I haven't even busted my
ass, and I'm already done, you
know what I mean?
>> I know it's a game where
it's everyone for himself, but
I really do have a lot of faith
in our tribe, and you kind of
have to look out for each other
if we want to do well at
challenges.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Fei Long, your first look at
the new Zhan Hu tribe.
Ashley voted out last night.
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge is
going to be another physical
confrontation.
Three on three.
You will start on opposite
sides of a boat.
On my go, you will engage in
hand-to-hand battle.
Your goal: throw the opposing
tribe members off the boat into
the water.
First tribe to get all the
tribe members of the other
tribe into the water scores a
point.
We will alternate, women on
women, men on men.
First tribe to get three points
wins reward.
You want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Comfort.
(applause)
>> Yeah!
>> We've got to win!
>> PROBST: Kerosene, a lantern,
rope, pillows, blankets, and
back here a big, ugly, but
functional tarp.
>> Tarp!
Yes!
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: Fei Long, you have
two extra members.
You're sitting two people out,
one man, one woman.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Who's going to sit
out?
The little ones.
>> The munchkins.
>> PROBST: Courtney and Todd
sitting out.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Okay, our first round is women
on women.
For Zhan Hu, we have Sherea,
Peih-gee, Jaime.
For Fei Long, we have Amanda,
Leslie, Denise.
Survivors ready?
Go!
(applause)
Sherea looking for a fight.
Denise making her move.
Denise has two women tied up.
Zhan Hu strikes first.
Fei Long down to two women now,
Leslie and Amanda.
Peih-gee and Leslie going at it.
Sherea and Jaime taking on
Amanda.
Amanda is in the water.
One woman left for Fei Long.
Leslie in.
Zhan Hu scores the first point.
Zhan Hu leads 1-0.
All right, men, take your spots.
Dave is stripping down.
>> Is he kidding me?
>> PROBST: It's either going
to give him an advantage or
make him very vulnerable.
For Zhan Hu, it's Frosti, Erik,
and Dave.
For Fei Long, James,
Jean-Robert, Aaron.
Zhan Hu leads 1-0.
Survivors ready?
Go.
James saying, "Come on over.
Come visit my boat."
Dave and Aaron on the gang
plank.
Dave like a little cat.
This is odd.
Dave attacks Aaron and pulls
him in.
>> Go, Dave!
>> PROBST: James tossing Frosti
in.
Erik is now taking on James and
Jean-Robert.
He's got no chance.
Jean-Robert takes him in.
James is the last man standing
for Fei Long.
We are tied 1-1.
Women on women again.
We are tied, 1-1.
It takes three to win.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Leslie on the gang plank.
Sherea on the gang plank.
Peih-gee and Amanda on the gang
plank.
We are about to engage.
Who's going to strike first?
Peih-gee goes at Amanda.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Peih-gee and Amanda
digging in.
Sherea comes over.
Sherea has Leslie.
Denise now getting in on it.
Jaime and Sherea push Leslie in.
Sherea now has Amanda by the
leg.
Peih-gee and Denise locking up.
Jaime and Sherea have Amanda.
>> Come on, girls, you can do
it.
>> PROBST: Jaime pushing her
head into the plank with her
knee.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Amanda takes Sherea
in with her.
Amanda's out.
Sherea is out.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah!
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Jaime and Peih-gee
push Denise in.
Zhan Hu scores and leads 2-1.
>> On!
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu leads 2-1,
playing to three.
It's men on men again.
Zhan Hu wins this round, they
win reward.
Dave, still naked.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Come on, you guys!
>> PROBST: Erik and Aaron
eyeing each other on the gang
plank.
Dave taunting the one guy you
don't want to taunt.
James and Dave really going at
it hard.
Jean-Robert and Frosti.
It is a melee.
It could be the last person in.
Dave is in, Frosti's in.
Jean-Robert is in.
Once again it's Erik wrapped
around the post.
Aaron and James working on him.
>> It's okay, Erik!
You got it!
>> PROBST: It is only a matter
of time now.
Aaron takes Erik in.
James is the last man standing
for Fei Long.
Fei Long scores.
We're tied 2-2.
>> Come on, girls!
>> PROBST: It comes down to the
women.
If history repeats, Zhan Hu
will win their first challenge.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Jaime and Peih-gee making the
move.
Jaime going after Denise.
Sherea locked up with Amanda.
Peih-gee locked up with Leslie.
This is it.
For reward!
Sherea pushing Amanda in.
Amanda hanging on.
Barely hanging on.
She's holding on to the leg of
Sherea, and that is it.
Amanda's in.
Fei Long down to two women left!
It is a big-time match-up.
Sherea using her lower body
strength.
Leslie's in the water.
Denise, the last woman from Fei
Long, fighting to stay in it.
Jaime, Peih-gee, Sherea,
working on Denise.
Sherea and Peih-gee, rolling
Denise off the plank.
Zhan Hu wins their first
challenge!
Zhan Hu, congratulations.
(cheers)
First win.
All the comfort.
In addition, because you won
this challenge, you will now
kidnap one member of Fei Long.
They will join you and live
with you until the next
immunity challenge.
Who are you going to steal?
>> Leslie.
>> PROBST: Leslie, cross right
over here.
>> Bye, Mom.
>> PROBST: Leslie, this is for
you.
It says, "open in private."
That's what it means.
Find a private spot.
Open it.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: That's all you need
to know.
Fei Long, I got nothing for you.
Head back to camp.
>> Welcome home!
>> Welcome home, little pillows!
>> I'm so excited.
Thanks.
I was so excited to win the
reward challenge.
Not only did we get pillows and
blankets and a tarp, we also
able to kidnap Leslie to our
tribe.
>> I'm really happy for you
guys, I am.
>> I appreciate that.
>> And I mean it.
>> You're genuine.
You can tell.
>> That's why we wanted you
over here.
>> That's why I'm going to
watch my mouth and keep my
drawers on just for you.
I have been anyway, but I'll be
even more so for you.
>> We're so glad you're here.
We have plenty of room for you.
>> We'll make you a nice dinner.
>> Morale-wise, this camp seems
to have a leg up.
And that's impressive
because they've already lost two
people.
And for them to be still so
excited, that's pretty
impressive.
(laughter)
>> Ooh!
That hurt watching that.
>> Yeah.
You know what, though, I think
we just have a lot of strong
personalities.
He's like my boy.
He calls me mama.
Yeah, he's nice.
>> He's nice, but he... he
controls a lot.
>> He's controlling, but we
elected him leader.
>> Why, is he really smart or
something?
>> He just kind of took over
when we got there.
>> We got quite a good bit of
information from Leslie, but it
was more in a kind of fun,
girls gossiping.
You can get the same results,
but you can do them in a happy,
nice way.
>> Uh-huh.
And Erik's a Christian and
Jaime's a Christian.
Wow.
I'm misunderstood over in my
tribe.
My faith is everything.
I'm here to love people and to
show them the love of Christ,
and I can see that they
appreciate that here.
It differs a lot over at Fei
Long.
I try not to talk about it a
lot over there.
They're very cynical over
there, and that can be really
tough.
>> The old woman is not going
to pull a rope.
She's going to be hurt.
>> Talking about Sister
Christian?
>> Yeah, Sister Christian.
She ain't going to last too
long.
And for some reason, you're all
buying that prayer stuff.
>> Come on, dude.
>> The people who pray the
most sin the most.
That's why they're praying.
Because they know they're going
to hell.
(laughter)
>> You got your strategy all
worked out, man?
>> You need to stay, Denise
needs to stay, and I need to
stay for a while.
>> I feel myself distancing
from Todd.
I felt kind of a bond with him
right away, but he's, like,
kind of tuned me out.
And Courtney, of course, I'm
not in with.
But I'm not worried about that
because she's going to be first
to go.
>> You think?
>> I mean, who else would be
first to go?
Denise or Courtney?
>> Courtney and I were cutting
this husk for a fire off of a
tree, and we were literally,
you know, 20 yards away from
Jean-Robert and James, in full
view, and they were talking at
the top of their lungs about
how Courtney needs to go first.
I'm thinking, "Dude, she's
right here."
>> Ooh!
Another clam.
>> Dude, who should we be
voting, Leslie or Courtney?
>> Courtney does work.
>> What do you mean she's does
work?
What does she do?
>> She moves stuff.
>> Look at what she's moving.
She's moving, like, two twigs.
Plus, you like Courtney.
A million dollars is one
thing but if you can get a
million dollars and some ass.
Come on, James.
You know you like that little
70-pound blonde.
Come on, man.
The only thing better than a
million dollars is a million
dollars and some ass.
Come on, now.
>> The only thing better than a
million dollars is a million
dollars and a sandwich.
>> All right, you know what?
Just for you, I'm going to
look out for you.
You stick with me, we're going
to do all right.
So we'll go for Leslie.
>> Oh, my attitude towards the
two of them is going to change
around camp.
Thank you, James.
You've got to take care of
taking out the trash.
And as far as I'm concerned,
James and Jean-Robert are the
trash.
>> All right, family.
Family swim.
Todd, you need to take your
stinky ass in the water, too.
>> I don't care if it's
tomorrow.
I don't care if it's five days
from now.
I don't care if it's nine days
Any more than that, trash gets
stinky.
They got to go.
>> Yesterday, at the reward
challenge, Jeff Probst gave me
a tube.
I kind of knew what was in the
tube because, when Jaime was
kidnapped by our camp, she had
the same thing.
"You must give the sealed clue
to a member of this tribe before
you rejoin your own tribe at
the next immunity challenge."
Hey, guys.
What I was thinking was, since
Jaime gave me the clue from the
other tribe, I can return the
favor.
Is there a place I can go and
change?
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> Like a place to...
>> You want me to go show you?
>> Yeah, would you mind?
>> I think I understand her.
I think she understands me.
And that's the best part.
I'm picking up what she's
putting down.
This is a good thing.
>> I trust Leslie more than
anyone else on the other team,
so it was really good to get
her over here.
And she gave me the clue for
the hidden immunity idol.
So altogether, it worked out
really well for me.
>> Yeah, these are closer.
The longer part.
>> "Hidden immunity idol clue
number one.
What is thought to be hidden may
sometimes be seen.
Though their eyes are not,
yours must be keen.
Hidden immunity idol clue number
two: waste no more time in
searching the ground.
Towards the heavens for what
will be found."
We have two clues, and I can't
figure out them quite yet.
I don't know, I think it's
something completely evident
that no one's just even paid
attention to.
I think it's probably right in
front of my face.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Leslie, give me the lowdown.
How was it spending time with
Zhan Hu?
>> Oh, they were great.
We talked a lot, laughed a lot.
It was fun.
We had a good time.
>> PROBST: All right, time to
rejoin Fei Long.
>> Have fun, you guys.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first,
take back the immunity idol.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
designate four choppers, two
puzzle builders.
The four choppers will race one
at a time to cut through wooden
beams concealing ropes,
releasing a bundle of wooden
disks.
When you have the disks, you'll
race back to your tribe.
The next person will go.
Once you've retrieved all four
bundles, the remaining two
tribe members must then stack
those disks in the correct
order on a puzzle pole with a
very heavy stone base.
You must then drag the
completed puzzle across the
finish line.
First tribe to finish wins
immunity, safe from tribal
council.
Losers, somebody voted out
tonight.
Fei Long, you have two extra
members.
Cannot sit out the same people
in back-to-back challenges,
which means Todd and Courtney
will participate in this
challenge.
Who you sitting out?
>> We're going to sit out
Denise and Leslie.
>> PROBST: Denise and Leslie
are going to sit out.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategy.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
Jaime first out for Zhan Hu.
Courtney first out for Fei Long.
>> Whoo!
>> Swing it in there!
>> Keep going, Courtney.
>> Concentrate!
>> All right, all right, keep
it up!
>> PROBST: Once you cut through
all seven ropes, you'll release
the bundle of disks.
>> Yeah!
(applause)
>> PROBST: Jaime has her first
bundle of disks.
Peih-gee now out on the course.
>> I'm sorry, guys.
>> That's all right, sweetie,
just keep going.
>> Come on, Courtney.
You gotta do it for us.
Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Peih-gee with only
three ropes left.
Peih-gee working on that last
rope.
There it is, chop it down.
Peih-gee has the second bundle
for Zhan Hu.
>> Damn.
>> How are they doing this?
>> Just keep going!
Don't look at them.
>> Frosti, ninja man.
>> PROBST: Frosti wasting no
time, attacking it.
Courtney still working on Fei
Long's first station.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Frosti, one swing
and he has his bundle.
Zhan Hu now with three bundles.
>> Come on, Erik!
>> PROBST: Erik starts to work
on his ropes.
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: Courtney, there is a
long puzzle to complete.
Do not give up.
Erik ripping through these
ropes.
One more, there it is.
Zhan Hu has all four bundles.
They can start work on their
puzzle.
>> Keep chopping, keep chopping.
That's good.
Slice it, yes, like that, slice
it.
>> PROBST: Courtney, sawing
through it now.
One chop left.
>> Big whack, big whack!
You have to saw through it.
>> That one.
>> PROBST: Courtney has her
first bundle!
>> Come on, let's go, let's go,
let's go!
>> Let's go, Amanda!
>> PROBST: Dave and Sherea not
having a lot of luck with the
puzzle.
It's going very slowly.
>> Eight, eight.
>> PROBST: Amanda working
through the rope quickly.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> Amanda, you go, girl!
>> PROBST: Amanda has the
second bundle for Fei Long.
Fei Long back in it now.
Aaron goes to town.
Zhan Hu having no luck on that
puzzle.
>> Upside down.
Can it be upside down?
Okay.
>> PROBST: Aaron quickly
through five ropes, six, and
seven.
Here it comes.
Fei Long is back in this
challenge.
>> All right, you all speed it
up a little bit.
>> Let's go, James!
>> PROBST: That is why you
never quit.
James has it.
Fei Long has all four bundles.
They can start work on their
puzzles.
>> Go, go.
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu has given up
nearly all of their lead.
>> You got it, baby!
>> PROBST: Which tribe chose
the right people to do the
right part of the challenge?
>> There you go!
>> PROBST: Todd making quick
work, working with Jean-Robert.
Zhan Hu seems to have a rhythm
now.
>> Get that off my finger!
>> PROBST: Sherea and Dave
working together, not panicking.
>> Got it.
>> What the hell, dude?
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu has the
puzzle completed.
They've just got to drag it
across the finish line.
>> Yeah!
Whoo!
Go!
>> PROBST: This puzzle is very
heavy.
>> Come on, girl!
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu on their way
to their first immunity win.
Zhan Hu wins immunity!
(cheers)
>> Oh, my god, girl!
Oh, my God!
Oh! Oh!
>> PROBST: Congratulations,
Zhan Hu.
For the first time, immunity
will be going back to camp with
you.
>> Yes!
>> It will look good on our
fireplace.
>> PROBST: And for the first
time, Fei Long will be going to
tribal council tonight, where
one of the eight of you will be
voted out.
Head on back to camp.
>> Did you hurt your shoulder,
too?
>> Yeah.
>> You did really well, baby
doll.
>> Yes, she did.
>> You didn't give up, which is
key.
>> We almost had them at the
end.
>> We did.
>> Losing today's challenge and
yesterday's challenge just kind
of reaffirms the fact that we
need strength.
We need brawn on our team.
So, I think common sense will
prevail and they're going to be
getting rid of one of the two
weakest women on the squad.
>> It's horrible.
They sting.
>> What's up with the other
tribe?
>> I think they're all, like,
friendly over there.
It's a very friendly tribe.
Three of them are Christians
over there, which is I think
why they picked me.
Three of them are Christians.
>> Which ones?
>> Sherea and Jaime and Erik.
>> What did they think about us?
>> They didn't really know a
whole lot about you.
I told them little bits about
you guys.
I said Aaron's our leader,
whether he likes it or not.
They knew.
They could tell.
>> You put my head in the
guillotine.
>> No, I didn't, they knew!
>> They knew?
>> They knew!
Jaime told them.
Come on.
>> Leslie going over to Zhan
Hu, being kidnapped, major
liability for us.
You know, she doesn't, she
doesn't think, you know,
because I don't know if it's
her heart or what, just
overcomes her brain.
But really what scares me is
once the merge happens, you
know, what kind of bond is
Leslie going to be involved
with because you can't, can't
really trust her.
>> I mean, I'm trying, and the
thing is, if we had a nice camp,
I think I could put up with the
challenges and this.
But, like, our camp is
miserable.
>> You mean the people?
>> Yeah.
>> So if we didn't have
Jean-Robert, how would that
change your life?
>> Jean-Robert and James have
to go.
>> We ought to bust those two
up.
>> So you guys are going for
Jean-Robert, right?
>> Yes, I mean, I promised I
would.
>> Okay, I'm go to leave you
guys.
I just wanted to...
>> We ought to break those two
up.
They're causing trouble.
But, Courtney, I'm worried
about you.
>> We have to think about later
in the game.
>> She'll be a vote for us.
We need her.
Do you really think we'll lose
a lot of challenges without
Jean-Robert?
It's not like we're getting rid
of James and Aaron.
So...
>> I don't want to vote Jean-
Robert out because of the
challenges.
You know, people will try and
find, you know, the tie that
binds, you know, so...
I want to be around a while.
I don't want to go to the
merger and get picked off.
>> He can easily, easily, jump
over to someone else's side...
>> I'm sure.
>> ...and pick us off one by
one to get him one step further.
>> Right, and I just feel
Leslie is more dangerous than
Jean-Robert in that jumping
way.
So we need to take her out.
>> Right now, it would be
between Leslie and Jean-Robert,
but further down the line, I
don't want to be competing, me
up against these huge guys.
I don't want to lose my numbers
on my tribe by getting rid of
them now, but down the line, I
don't want them here because
they're going to beat me, and
that's not okay.
>> Tonight we're going to have
a vote, and the logical choice
for us to let someone go is to
let one of our two weaker
players go.
Which, obviously, is Courtney
and Leslie.
Leslie seems to be breaking
down every single day, and then
Courtney, seriously, even if
she makes it past today or, I
don't see how this girl is
going to live 30 days.
I've seen anorexic girls have
more meat on their bones than
this girl has.
To me, we're just lucky they
didn't tell us one girl and
one guy have to sit out today.
That would have been really
brutal.
>> How are your hands?
>> This game is not just
physical right now.
I'm trying to think
strategically as well.
It does bug me that Leslie was
so excited to go over to the
other tribe.
And, yeah, who knows what she's
plotting with people over there.
And... I don't know.
I want to get rid of
Jean-Robert but at the same
time, as far as challenges go,
I want to keep Jean-Robert.
But who knows?
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach the flame.
This is part of the ritual of
tribal council because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire,
you're still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
That will be the case for one
of you tonight.
So, let's talk about the
challenges.
You guys started off very
strong.
Three wins in a row.
Then, back-to-back losses.
Zhan Hu knows they can beat
this tribe.
Jean-Robert, a little concerned?
>> Very concerned.
You know, you look at our
group, and, yeah, we might have
two of the three biggest guys
in the whole thing, but we also
have two of the weakest girls,
and that's just, that's just a
matter of fact.
>> PROBST: Who are the two weak?
Obviously, you're going to be
pointing to Courtney because
she's the smallest.
>> Courtney and Leslie is who I
am referring to.
>> This is fun to live with.
>> This is the reality of the
situation.
This is our team.
So we should be very careful
who we sit out so we're left
with a more balanced team each
time.
>> PROBST: Courtney, that can't
feel good to hear.
>> For the past nine days, it's
like how can we possibly get
Courtney and Todd and Leslie
to not play.
And I'm like a little Chihuahua
trying to run a horse race so
far.
Everything is like mud
wrestling, or like winging
people off a boat.
They're like, "Crap, we have
to put her in.
Where will she do the least
damage?"
And I'm like, "I don't give a
crap."
I'm just sick of being spoken
of, like, "Where will you do
the least damage in this
challenge?"
>> That's not what we were
thinking.
>> That's how it comes across
day after day.
>> It's not that I perceive
Leslie as weak or Courtney as
weak.
To be honest...
>> PROBST: Jean-Robert, that is
exactly what you said.
>> Okay, the weaker of this
group.
It's the reality of the
situation.
I'm not going to sugarcoat it.
When it comes to the three
strongest girls, it is clearly
Denise, Amanda and then who?
We're playing for a million
dollars here.
We're not babies in a
campground.
Feelings are going to get hurt
or they're not going to get
hurt.
I'm not known for holding my
thoughts back.
I'm going to say exactly what I
think but I'm keeping it real.
>> Can I say something?
I spent a night with Zhan Hu.
And I saw not a strong physical
tribe but a strong heart.
They're united.
They do things together.
They have fun.
You know, we may have all the
brawn in the world, but if we
don't have heart, we're not
going to make it.
Those people won that challenge
because of this, not because of
this.
>> PROBST: Jean-Robert, you at
all concerned it might be you
tonight?
>> Well, of course I'm
concerned it could be me.
To be honest with you, Jeff,
the heat's been on since day
two.
And somehow, the last few days,
I've shown a little bit more,
and I've pretty much kicked
some butt in the challenges.
So tonight, my chances are a
little bit fair, but I'm still
in jeopardy.
I would say I'm definitely one
of the two or three people
that's in jeopardy in this tribe
and I'm really hoping to make it
through tonight.
>> PROBST: All right, it is
time to vote.
Aaron, you're up.
>> Sorry, mother hen.
All your chicks in China are
grown up.
>> I'm voting for you because,
when you snore at nighttime, it
sounds like someone is choking
a walrus.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jean-Robert.
Leslie.
One vote Leslie.
Jean-Robert.
Two votes Jean-Robert.
Sister Christian.
That's Leslie.
We're tied, two votes Jean-
Robert, two votes Leslie.
Leslie.
That's three votes Leslie, two
votes Jean-Robert.
Mom.
That's Leslie.
That's four votes Leslie, two
votes Jean-Robert.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: China, Leslie.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Leslie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Well, it seems like
the big themes from tonight's
tribal council are this tribe
needs to have a little more
fun, and this tribe needs to do
a better job of utilizing each
person's unique strength.
Grab your torches, head back
to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> Don't touch that.
Don't touch that.
>> PROBST: ...at Fei Long,
things heat up between Courtney
and Jean-Robert.
>> If Courtney survives the
next tribal council, she's got
to be the luckiest girl in
Survivor history.
>> PROBST: At Zhan Hu, Sherea
blows her cool.
>> Don't walk up on me again.
>> PROBST: And both tribes get
a lesson in the art of war.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> I am so proud of myself.
I had this dream.
I chased the dream, and I would
have liked to have been here
longer, of course, but I always
knew going into this game that
I would be here as long as God
wanted me to be here.
Apparently, He's ready for me
to go home.
I don't understand why they
vote me out, but I really hope
that my tribe made the right
decision.
It had to have been a tough one
for them.
But I had a great time.
I would do it again in a
heartbeat.