>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
16 Americans began the
adventure of a lifetime in
modern Shanghai.
They traveled back in time to a
remote section of rural China.
At a Buddhist welcoming
ceremony, Leslie was faced with
a moral dilemma.
>> I'm a believer in Jesus
Christ, and in the Bible it
says "Thou shall not bow down
to any other god."
I just couldn't do it.
>> PROBST: The survivors were
split into two tribes, Zhan Hu
and Fei Long.
After a heavy storm pounded the
Zhan Hu tribe, Ashley, the
professional wrestler, was down
for the count.
>> I want to throw up, but
there's just nothing in there.
>> PROBST: Chicken was
unimpressed with his tribe.
>> You think this here's going
to hold up?
>> We have to build something,
though, so let's stop being
negative.
>> I'm giving my opinion and
nobody wants it, so I'm done
suggesting.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, back at
Fei Long, Todd nominated Aaron
as tribe leader.
>> We do need someone who is
strong and smart.
>> It feels weird, but I think
I can do it.
>> I am very, very smart in
trying push the leader role
more so on to Aaron.
>> PROBST: At the first immunity
challenge...
Neck and neck going into the
swamp.
...Fei Long came out on top...
Fei Long wins immunity!
...sending Zhan Hu to tribal
council.
Anybody here willing to say, "I
will be the leader of this
tribe?"
There's your leader.
Well, now you got two.
Dave and Peih-gee volunteered
to lead their tribe.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: And in the end,
Ashley was spared.
First person voted out of
Survivor: China-- Chicken.
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: 15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> The fire pit has to be done
properly the first time.
We can't have any more oopsies
like we did with the shelter.
The shelter is one thing.
Man, once you do a fire pit,
we just got to do it once and
do it right.
Last night at tribal council,
questions came up about
leadership.
I raised my hand to say, "Heck,
I'll do it."
I didn't want to be in a
leadership role, but instead of
resisting things like that,
especially with the people in
my tribe, I think it's
actually better to embrace it.
I think pull this dead pine tree
out of the way, plopping the
bricks down right here.
>> I just kind of don't want to
sit next to the woods.
We could put where our water
collection is, and we'll just
move.
>> Yeah.
I think that will be good.
>> Uh-uh.
>> I mean, it will really help
with the insects.
>> I want more shelter for the
fire.
Putting it right there on the
edge?
No, I don't think that's a
great idea at all.
Okay.
We're moving forward.
I don't want to start
belaboring this kind of stuff
because it sucks a lot of time
and energy away from getting
stuff done.
>> Dave and I work pretty well
together.
We both kind of do it in
different ways, but if
anything, we're not being
competitive about, like, who
can be, like, leader.
>> I'm just trying to explain
the sensibility of why I think
it.
If someone can think of
something different...
>> No, no, you had valid
reasons for putting it over
there.
And you know what?
For me, like, if you have
definite experience that it will
work better over there, I'll
totally go with it.
>> It seems that Dave is kind
of the leader, the top guy, and
Peih-gee is just below him.
She's kind of like the balance
of power.
>> I think we've got like a
game plan...
>> We do.
>> ...set in place.
We can figure out who's going
to do what.
But most important is knowing
what the what is, you know.
>> Dave has a lot of good
ideas, but if someone questions
it or if somebody comes up with
their own idea, there is this
sense that he's probably still
going to go with his idea.
>> If we could get our act
together and do this fast this
morning and eat before our
possible challenge this
afternoon, we'd be rocking.
>> You're wishing really hard,
Jaime, I'll tell you that right
now.
You're wishing really hard.
>> You should wish hard.
>> Okay, fine.
>> It could get to the point
where people start getting fed
up and start talking about Dave
and how they don't necessarily
think he's a good leader
anymore.
>> This is where it begins right
here.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
(snoring)
>> All right, Jean-Robert's
snoring goes something like
this...
(imitates Jean-Robert snoring)
Jean-Robert, we all know he's
like the "D" student of our
tribe.
He won't do anything.
He gets up and instantly has to
lay down because he's so tired.
>> Oh, man, I'm about to pass
out.
>> I will stick with you
because you know this game.
>> You're my one alliance, too.
You have to have one in this
game.
You have to.
Me and Todd made an alliance
that we're going to stick it out
with each other until the end of
this because even though Todd, I
think, is very devious, I've
been watching him really
closely and I think we have a
good alliance so far, at
least until the merge.
>> At some point, should we
pull him in as number three?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Because we need someone
strong to call our shots.
We make the plans and he speaks
them out, which puts the target
on him instead of us.
>> We decided to pull Aaron
into our group, so if anyone
has to take a rap for anything,
then it's going to be on Aaron.
>> Obviously, this is about
power players, right, and who
wants to go the furthest.
We need a three.
>> Which is us.
>> I think that would be smart.
>> Like, I will swear to you
guys with my whole life.
>> Three?
>> I will, too.
>> Okay.
>> Because that's how the game
is played.
You know, you have to.
>> The final three.
>> At that point, I mean, it's
sad to say, it's game on.
>> I trust.
>> I trust, too.
>> Amanda and I have this game
in our hands.
So we have our alliance.
We have exactly what I wanted
to come here to do.
>> You guys want to powwow?
So, a lot harder than what we
thought, huh?
Three sleepless nights,
everyone's on edge.
Everyone's angry.
We have to get into some sort
of routine.
>> Why don't we just all rest?
Now's a good time to get
refreshed.
>> Jean-Robert, you need to
start pulling your weight.
This is what I feel, not
whether I'm right or wrong.
You might want to talk about it.
>> I know that I'm not working
as much as I'd like to be able
to work, just because I've
slept a little bit less than
everybody, I think.
>> Jean-Robert needs to step it
up.
What is up with this guy?
He knows he's on the chopping
block, and it's pretty obvious
around camp.
He's trying to divert it, but
we're not buying it.
>> The wheels are turning here.
Believe me, I can contribute
probably as valuable of stuff
with my mind.
But, I mean, as soon as we
start getting food and water
and everything, I think you're
going to find I'm able to
contribute a lot more.
I'm considered one of the bad
boys of poker.
And I absolutely am using a
similar strategy in this
Survivor game.
I wanted to give the perception
I was a little bit lazy, so
later when I am contributing
and putting in the work effort,
people are noticing, "Hey, this
guy is doing beyond his normal
capabilities."
I know that I'd like to be able
to do a lot more than I am,
but, I mean, we've got a great
squad.
Even though it looks like I'm
in big trouble right now, it's
kind of part of the plan.
I can only go up from here.
>> Our biggest priority right
now are mud bricks.
I have specific goals.
We still have some shelter
stuff to fix, but we have
enough shelter.
I think that's all right.
The priority now we have flint
is to get a fireplace going.
It's a very realistic and
achievable goal today.
I want to keep goals achievable.
>> We need seven more.
Do you think there's any
possible way to at least start
a baby fire?
If we could get a spark started
up, we could put it under
something, just keep it alive.
>> You know what?
I would rather get some of it
up and then get a fire started.
>> All I asked was to make a
little baby fire to make a
handful of rice for everybody.
Instead, we try to build an
elaborate barbecue pit.
I'm not too thrilled about it.
>> Oh, wow, I'm so sorry.
I just totally hosed both of
you.
>> That's fine.
>> Ashley.
>> Oh, my gosh, what happened?
>> Dave drops the brick down
and splashes her.
>> Obviously he did it on
purpose.
I'd like to go steal the flint,
go out there and make me a
little fire and cook some rice.
>> We got the flint last night
at tribal council, and we
haven't even attempted to make a
fire.
And we're starving.
It just seems like we take the
longest route possible to make
something happen.
I'm losing faith rapidly.
>> Nothing here has wasted
energy.
I moved half those stones
myself just now.
>> Okay.
>> So if you can imagine...
>> So why don't we start the
fire...
>> Let me finish.
>> ...in the fireplace.
Mud bricks yea high.
I'm not stacking mud bricks
around a burning fire.
>> Mud bricks or not, you can
still try and get the fire
going before the rain starts
falling.
The rain's going to fall.
But you're the leader, and I'm
going to let you do what you
want.
>> I want to have shelter so it
stays lit, Ashley.
How many fires have you built,
sweetheart?
>> I'm just saying.
I'm tired.
I'm hungry.
>> Who isn't?
>> I just feel like four days
later, we don't have anything.
>> I don't want to fight with
Ashley.
If she wants to fight, I can
give her a fight.
The rest of the team's great.
Ashley...
Do you need to yell?
>> No, I'm not trying to yell.
>> But you are.
>> I said, "I'm tired, I'm
thirsty," and you said, "Well,
don't you think everyone else
is?"
Of course everybody else is.
Did I say they weren't?
Why are you trying to make me
sound like I'm just
completely...
>> Just keep going.
>> Okay, that's what he want me
to do.
>> No, I don't.
>> Okay.
>> I'm not trying to finger
anybody.
I want the fire done.
You're hungry.
Ash, stop bitching.
>> I'm not bitching.
I just would like to eat today
and I think everybody else is
saying the same thing.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Prepare to get dirty.
Fei Long getting your first
look at the new Zhan Hu tribe.
Chicken voted out at the first
tribal council.
All right, you guys ready to
get to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, here's how
it's going to work: you're
going to square off, three on
three.
I'm going to release two giant
wooden balls into this mud pit.
Your objective is to push
either one of those two balls
across your opponents' goal.
Each time you do, you score
a point for your tribe.
First tribe to score two points
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
To go along with the fire,
fishing gear.
In addition, you will have a
fishing boat waiting for you at
camp.
There is one other twist to
this reward that will be
revealed after the challenge is
over.
Make sense?
>> Yep.
>> Yes.
>> Fei Long, because this
challenge requires equal
numbers of men and women, you
have to sit out a man.
James doesn't even hesitate,
points at Todd.
>> I'm the smallest out of us.
>> PROBST: You all right with
that?
>> Yep, let's do it.
>> We love you, Todd.
>> PROBST: Todd, you're going to
take a spot on the bench.
First round will be two women,
one man.
Give you a minute to
strategize, we'll get started.
Here we go.
Just like we like it on
Survivor, nice and wet.
First round, Aaron, Amanda,
Denise taking on Sherea, Erik
and Jaime.
Go!
Aaron's got a free shot.
Erik and Sherea are back on him
now.
Now it's Amanda with a free run.
Jaime trying to stay on her.
The women doing a very good job
for Zhan Hu.
Sherea takes Denise down.
Amanda switching balls now.
Nobody defending.
Jaime making her way slowly
towards the goal.
Aaron having nothing to do with
it.
Sherea now getting back in it.
Aaron has his arms around
Jaime and Sherea, takes them
both down in the water.
Amanda now trying to take
advantage of the situation.
Amanda has a free shot.
Sherea now trying to get Amanda
off.
Denise puts both arms around
Jaime and pulls her out.
Aaron's got a free shot now.
Erik's going to have to defend.
Jaime pulls off Denise's shoe
and throws it.
Sherea trying pull Amanda's top
completely off.
Everybody pulling everybody's
clothes off now.
Amanda not letting it get in her
way.
Aaron's pulled Erik off the
ball.
Amanda has a free shot at the
Fei Long scores first goal!
>> Put your top back on, Amanda!
>> PROBST: Even with no top on,
Amanda scores for Fei Long.
Next round, Jean-Robert, James
and Leslie taking on Frosti,
Ashley and Dave.
Fei Long leads 1-0.
They score one more point, they
win.
Go!
James and Frosti going at it.
Jean-Robert with a free shot at
the ball.
Ashley getting in on it now.
James takes Frosti down.
Leslie pulling off Dave.
Jean-Robert muscling his way to
the end.
Ashley cannot stop him.
Frosti jumps on Jean-Robert.
Keeping it wide open for James.
Frosti holding on for dear life.
Jean-Robert pulls off Frosti.
This is close to being over.
Fei Long wins!
>> We're going fishing tonight,
baby.
(cheers)
>> PROBST: Fei Long,
congratulations.
Two challenges, two wins.
Not bad.
You have the ability to make
fire.
You have the tools to catch
fish.
It should start to change your
lives a little bit.
Now to the twist.
Fei Long, because you defeated
Zhan Hu, you now get to kidnap
one member of their tribe.
That person will come and live
with you until the next
immunity challenge.
Who are you going to kidnap?
>> Jaime.
>> PROBST: All right, Jaime.
You're going to leave here now.
You'll go with Fei Long, live
at their camp.
You will return at the next
immunity challenge and rejoin
your tribe.
There's one more layer to this
twist, Jaime-- this is for you.
It says "open in private."
When you get to their beach,
find a private spot and read it.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Come get it.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu, I got
nothing for you.
Get your stuff, head on back to
camp.
Fei Long, take your new tribe
member, head on back to camp.
>> I cannot believe it rained
this much.
Like, it didn't seem like it
rained this much, did it?
>> It looks like a natural
disaster hit our camp.
This is basically destroyed.
>> It's like somebody just took
all the water from every ocean
they could find and just poured
it right on top of us.
>> We actually live on the lake
now.
>> Oh, my god.
>> At least the bricks are
above the water level.
I'm really happy I took the
time to build the pit versus
the fire first because this just
goes to show that I actually had
a fairly sound idea and I'm
glad I stuck with it and I
think it was worth the time.
Keep this piece, perhaps, right
over here.
>> This is so good.
Fei Long.
>> A fishing boat.
>> So, who's going fishing?
>> You are.
>> We are.
>> Fei Long tribe.
At the reward challenge, we
won fishing gear and a fishing
boat.
After the challenge, we picked
Jaime to kidnap because she is
a spot of sunshine in the tribe.
Taking away Jaime from Zhan Hu
completely demoralizes them.
>> Yes, we got to keep track of
everything.
>> Keep track of everything,
because in The Art of War, it
talks about stealing things
from your opponent.
>> Todd is a sharp kid and his
head is in the game.
So I want Todd on my side
because I think we work well
together as a team.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Jean-Robert.
>> Jaime.
>> I just got put with a
different tribe.
They picked me and then Jeff
gave me this to go with it.
"Read this note but do not open
the bamboo tube.
Before making an alliance with
a neighbor, you must understand
his intentions.
In this sealed tube is a clue to
a hidden immunity idol at the
enemy camp.
You must give this sealed
clue to a member of this
tribe before you rejoin your
own tribe at the next
immunity challenge."
The note actually has a clue for
the other team and it lets them
know where the immunity idol
is, so I am allowed to pick any
member of the team I want and
give it to them.
>> Now that's a fire.
>> You know, Aaron, you're quick
to jump on my ass about
anything.
You know that.
>> I know.
We don't like each other.
>> You're not right about that.
>> You like me and I don't like
you?
>> There you go.
>> Okay.
>> Jean-Robert and Aaron got
into a ridiculous bitch fight.
And we were all just like,
(sighs), "In front of the spy?
Really?
Are you just going to give
her a map of who doesn't like
who?
Can we not have, like, a little
solidarity for like two seconds
while she's here.
>> Let's go around the camp and
ask who's doing a good job.
>> You know what?
>> What?
>> I didn't want to do battle
with you, but you're making me
have no choice.
>> When I go back to my team,
I'm telling them, "I don't know
why the heck we're not winning,
because when I've seen what
I've seen, we should be
winning."
>> I'm going to put four
bricks in there and then grab
some of this mud and just pour
it in there like mortar, and it
will dry and be stable.
>> So, what should I have done?
>> Break up some wood.
>> All of this has to be broken
down.
All that should be broken down.
>> All right, let me do one
thing at a time.
I get overwhelmed.
I don't like that.
>> It's all the same thing.
It's the one thing.
I'm showing you three different
spots to find it, that's all.
>> You don't have to be mean to
me.
Why do you have to have such an
attitude sometimes?
>> It's not overwhelming.
I'm telling you where to find
the resources for the one thing
you're doing.
>> Okay, but you're doing it
with an attitude.
I don't know why, it just comes
naturally.
>> Okay, I apologize.
>> You're always like grr, grr,
grr.
>> Apologies.
>> Can I finish my sentence?
>> After you interrupted me
when I was talking mine?
>> I'm literally just asking
you what you want me to do.
>> I do think that Dave is wrong
in the way he talks down to
Ashley, telling her what to do,
you know?
You can't boss adults around,
really, not too much, without
pissing them off.
>> Can we both right now get
this pile and this pile done?
>> But where are we going to
get it done to?
>> I said it already this
morning at least a couple times.
>> Is there any dry place in
this entire area that we
could...
>> Think outside the box.
Critical and analytical
thinking really helps.
>> I don't need your life
lessons.
I just need you to tell me what
to do.
>> Later.
>> Adios.
>> I believe that Dave's going
to shoot himself in the foot.
He's not a good leader because
he's the most irritating person
on the planet.
He's just so patronizing.
>> The last few days, I have
been really sick.
I just feel dirty.
I feel miserable.
It's just hard because I don't
have my Bible.
I know if I could read it and
just spend some time with God,
it would be great.
But I mean, he has me here for
a reason, so I'm going to keep
fighting.
>> My strategy as far as the
clue goes is I'm going to give
it to whom I think is their
weakest link, just so I keep
their team weaker.
>> Don't let anybody know you
have it.
>> Okay.
>> I feel like the Lord really
gave me a gift with the clue
to the hidden immunity idol.
Wow, this is a really big deal.
"Hidden immunity idol clue
number one.
What is thought to be hidden
may sometimes be seen.
Though their eyes are not,
yours must be keen."
Hmm.
I feel really confident that I
can find the hidden immunity
idol.
In the clue, it said it's
obvious.
And I think, you know, this is
probably something you see every
day and would never consider
that it would be a hidden
immunity idol.
>> I'm looking everywhere for
the hidden immunity idol,
looking for something that would
be obvious.
My mom used to always say, "If
it was a snake, it would have
bit you."
And I feel like that's what it's
like.
Like, if it was a snake, it
would have bit me by now.
I think what I really want do
with this information I have is
use it to gain's someone trust,
so it has to be someone who's
witty, somebody who can think
and Todd's pretty witty.
So, I want to team up with him.
>> It said that is was obvious.
I told Todd the idol is here.
So we're going to team up and
use it together.
And I trust him.
>> Okay.
Here comes some people,
so...
>> Morning, guys.
>> I can't believe she told me.
I'm in shock.
I would never tell anybody.
What was she thinking?
Leslie's sick, so if she goes,
I'll be the only one that knows
about it.
So my goal is to find that
thing as fast as I can, and if
Leslie gets sick and has to
leave, I'm the only one that
knows about it.
Fantastic.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Back for more punishment.
Fei Long, come on in.
So, Jaime, tell me about your
time at Fei Long.
>> Well, they made it the best
it could be, so I appreciate it.
>> PROBST: Jaime, your time over
there is done.
Get back over to Zhan Hu.
(applause)
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
First things first-- Amanda,
I'll take back the immunity
idol.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, each
tribe will use a large Chinese
puzzle log to smash through two
tribe-colored walls.
Once you're through both walls,
you must then maneuver the log
through the maze carved into
the outside of the puzzle log.
First tribe to get their log
through the maze and ring the
gong wins immunity, safe from
tonight's tribal council.
Losers, another person will
be voted out.
Make sense?
Because this challenge runs six
on six, both tribes will be
sitting people out.
Zhan Hu, you have one extra
member.
Who are you going to sit out?
>> Jaime will sit out.
>> PROBST: Jaime's going to sit
out.
Fei Long, you have two extra
members, who are you going to
sit out?
>> Courtney and Leslie.
>> PROBST: Courtney and
Leslie.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize and we'll
get started.
Here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready.
Go!
Both tribes with good
rhythm.
Fei Long working together well.
Fei Long is through first.
Zhan Hu go.
Both tribes through.
Fei Long with a bit of a lead.
>> We got four.
>> Hold on, hold on.
Ready, one, two, three!
>> PROBST: Fei Long has a good
rhythm.
Working together well.
Zhan Hu wearing out.
Dave can barely move that log
anymore.
Frosti bringing up the rear.
Fei Long doing great work on
their wall.
You're through!
Fei Long is through.
>> Keep it up, guys.
>> PROBST: That log is throwing
Dave around.
Zhan Hu wearing out.
>> Dave, switch with me.
>> Pick it up, Dave.
>> PROBST: Frosti switching with
Dave.
Dave, get a hold of the log.
Get it.
You're still in it!
Fei Long working together as a
tribe.
>> Get it up there, get it up
there.
>> Listen to Aaron.
Listen to Aaron.
>> PROBST: You guys need dig
deep.
Let's go.
There you go.
You're through.
Zhan Hu's through.
>> Come on, guys!
You guys better run.
>> PROBST: Fei Long already
working.
Zhan Hu now catching up.
It only goes through one way.
>> Keep going around.
>> PROBST: Fei Long with a bit
of a lead.
Zhan Hu trying to catch up.
Fei Long reaches a dead end.
They got to back it up now.
>> Forward, back, back, back.
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu now in the
lead.
>> Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
>> PROBST: Fei Long taking their
time.
Nobody panicking on Fei Long.
>> It's a dead end here.
>> PROBST: Zhan Hu reaches a
dead end.
>> Left.
>> There, go back.
>> PROBST: Fei Long in the lead
again.
Keep moving, Zhan Hu, keep
moving!
Zhan Hu falling behind.
Fei Long is very close.
Fei Long is through.
Fei Long wins immunity!
All right.
Fei Long, once again, immunity
is yours.
(applause)
Nobody going home from Fei Long.
Zhan Hu, all I got for you is
another date with me tonight at
tribal council, where one of the
seven of you will be voted out
of this game.
You have the afternoon to
figure out who it's going to be.
Head on back to camp.
See you at tribal.
Fei Long, head on out, guys.
Nice work.
>> I feel really bad because,
you know, we blew it today, and
I feel like I let the tribe
down.
Can I say something really
quick?
Please?
I apologize.
I feel like I let us down today
because I lost my footing and I
lost my rhythm, trying to get
my rhythm back, I lost my power.
>> Dave, you tried, but you
know what...
>> I'm sorry.
And Frosti, thank you so much
for stepping up and seeing what
was happening and switching
with me.
I take full responsibility for
the challenge today.
At the same time, the last six
days haven't been about one
challenge.
It's been about day in and day
out in camp and how you
contribute and what your
attitude's like.
I'm fairly confident how things
are going to go this evening.
You know, you reap what you sew.
Nothing's carved in stone yet,
but I'm pretty confident I'm
not going home.
>> I know that Dave is voting
for me at tonight's tribal
council.
At this point, I see my options
are this: I can either confront
everybody, act like a crazy
woman and say (inaudible)
and make myself look like an
idiot, or I could keep my head
together, go to tribal council
and tell everyone, like, "Look,
Dave is a crazy person."
>> I feel like if there's such
conflict with Dave and Ashley,
you know, if people are
targeting Ashley for that
reason, I guess it also makes
Dave a target.
If you had to pick between
those two, you might think
Dave, but I still see him as
strong.
Remove one of them and the
other one can stay around.
See what I'm saying?
It's probably dead even
between Ashley and Dave.
It puts me in a hard place
because Ashley is my friend,
but then Dave's such hard worker
and he knows what he's doing out
here.
So I'm not really sure what's
going to happen tonight.
>> PROBST: So, last time we
were here, we did a little
tribe therapy, and it appeared
that you had at least one
leader, maybe two.
Frosti, how is that leadership
working out?
>> Well, Dave's really stepped
up.
He was already giving some
leadership-type demands, and
he's really trying to do
everything.
At times, I fear he may attempt
too much.
>> It's a hard habit to kick.
>> PROBST: Ashley, you were
rolling your eyes.
>> Well, Dave and I kind of
butt heads sort of.
Our personalities just don't
mesh well.
But I respect him as a leader,
and when I have questions, I'll
ask them, even if I'm not
supposed to.
>> PROBST: And Dave, that rubs
you the wrong way?
>> It doesn't rub me the wrong
way at all.
Everyone is totally welcome to
ask questions.
If you're unclear on something,
then please do ask.
Because all I want to do is get
camp life fully squared away.
>> I don't expect Dave to say,
"Well, yeah, that's the way it's
been."
That's what he does-- he goes
off on rants and patronizes and
talks down to you and treats
you like a child.
>> PROBST: Ashley, do you think
this is just about you, or do
you notice it with other people,
as well?
>> I notice that other people
have a problem with it as well.
Dave talks in circles a lot,
and he always wants to be the
martyr.
The way he handles that
leadership, it's just, for me,
it's intolerable.
>> I'm incredibly rusty at
leadership, too.
This is a brand new boat for
me.
It's been a long time.
>> PROBST: Jaime, is there a
chance Dave's trying to prove
too much versus lead the tribe?
>> I think Dave is definitely
over the top trying to prove
himself.
I mean, you wake up and there's
already wood coming and it's
just, like, whoa, you know, slow
down for a second.
>> PROBST: Jaime, what does
this tribe need to do?
>> I personally think most of
us all get along.
These two just clash heads, and
I think sometimes the way you
phrase your demands, it might
intimidate people.
>> I've also asked everyone
here to check me if I have.
>> See, already, defense mode.
>> I'm out of line, please
check me because I need it.
>> For me, I know we have work
to do, but I haven't enjoyed
almost a single moment since
I've been here.
I barely know any of these
people.
I know Ashley, I know Jaime.
I'm dying to know Erik a little
better, but the other three, I
couldn't even tell you their
last names.
>> We're always working our
butts off.
>> That's my... did you not hear
what came out of my mouth?
Did you not hear what came out
of my mouth?
Never once have we sat down as
a tribe to talk about, well
what do we want to do as a
tribe?
How are we going to make this
come together?
How are we going to win?
Perfect example, again, Ashley,
every time she says something,
you have a comment back.
>> And now look what happened.
Now I'm on the chopping block.
>> PROBST: Ashley, what's the
criteria for your vote tonight?
>> I'm voting for Dave.
>> I expect more than one vote
tonight.
>> PROBST: Dave, how would the
tribe be better if it's Ashley
that's voted out tonight?
>> There will be a heck of a
lot less eggshells to walk
around on.
I only have conflict with
Ashley.
>> PROBST: Well, once again
we've had another good session
of tribe therapy.
It's time to vote.
Erik, you're up.
>> In a different setting and
circumstance, you might be
having (inaudible).
I wish you the best of luck.
>> I'm voting for Derek
Zoolander.
Oh, I mean Dave.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Ashley.
Dave.
One vote Ashley, one vote Dave.
Ashley.
Two votes Ashley, one vote Dave.
Three votes Ashley, one vote
Dave.
Second person voted out of
Survivor: China, Ashley.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> I'll see you soon.
>> PROBST: Ashley, the tribe has
spoken.
Time to go.
Grab your torches.
Head back the camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Dave loses patience with Zhan
Hu.
>> It's not rocket science.
>> PROBST: At Fei Long...
>> Courtney, of course, is going
to be first to go.
>> PROBST: ...Todd and Courtney
hear more than they bargain for.
>> Dude, she's right here.
>> PROBST: ...and the game gets
even more brutal.
(screaming)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> I think I got voted out
because of a personal conflict
with our leader, and Dave is
going to show them the reason
that he shouldn't be in
control, and I guarantee you
that I'll see him on the flip
side way sooner than he
imagines.
Dave, if I had one word to
describe him, he'd be "tool."
Because that is the perfect word
for him, he's a tool.