>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, at Zhan Hu, James was
doomed.
>> If we lose tomorrow's
immunity, James is going to be
gone.
>> PROBST: But at the reward
challenge...
Fei Long wins reward!
...Fei Long kidnapped their old
tribe mate, giving him a chance
to survive.
James, this is for you.
At Fei Long, James chose Todd to
receive the clue to the hidden
immunity idol.
>> I know what they're talking
about.
It's those stupid bats above the
freaking thing.
>> PROBST: Todd found the hidden
immunity idol, which was clearly
marked "Congratulations," and
gave it to James as part of his
and Amanda's plan to throw the
immunity challenge and take out
a Zhan Hu member.
>> Throw it.
>> Because that's Jaime's ticket
home.
James loses immunity; they vote
for him, but he uses the idol to
get rid of Jaime.
>> PROBST: He then told James
about the second idol hidden at
the Zhan Hu camp.
>> All I have to do is stay
focused, get the other idol.
Now I'll have both of them.
>> PROBST: But at the immunity
challenge...
Go.
>> Ah!
>> PROBST: ...Denise couldn't
stomach the chicken fetus...
>> I can't swallow it.
You can do it, James.
Eat it up.
>> PROBST: ...making it
impossible for James to
deliberately lose the challenge,
ruining Todd's plan.
Zhan Hu wins immunity.
With Fei Long facing tribal
council...
>> Genius idea smashed.
>> PROBST: ...Sherea seemed like
a sure bet to go home, but
Courtney lobbied to get rid of
Jean-Robert.
>> That's my enemy.
>> I don't trust Sherea.
I trust her more than I trust
Jean-Robert.
>> I feel like we should vote
out Jean-Robert tonight.
>> Todd, I don't know.
My gut feeling is that I don't
trust Sherea.
>> And my gut's saying Jean-
Robert.
This sucks.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Courtney attacked Jean-Robert's
character.
>> He walks around, he talks a
lot, a lot of judgments of other
people.
He's just a crappy person.
>> PROBST: Despite Courtney's
plea to get rid of Jean-Robert,
the tribe saved him once again.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: China, Sherea.
Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> That was a little bit of a
surprise.
I didn't even know there was
that kind of tension.
>> I promise you, Amanda, if
somebody did that to you, you'd
be a little bit upset about it
too.
>> I personally, Jean-Robert,
feel like my personal feelings
towards you have changed.
I like the guy you kind of
showed me who you can be.
I can't speak for Courtney, and
you can't speak for her.
And you know, I just... I
just... you guys have a tiff.
And if you guys resolve it,
that's what you guys can do.
If not, then not, you know?
>> Jean-Robert, he's horrible to
me.
He's not nice to me.
They suck up to him, even the
two people who want to be, like,
my friends-- like, "friends"--
Todd and Amanda.
I don't feel like I really need
to be anybody's friend in this
game.
I dislike everyone else more
than I dislike Todd and Amanda.
I think they mistake that for
friendship.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> James, I hope you trust us
now, because we told you we were
going to stick with you.
You know that?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, to each other, yeah.
>> Don't let me down, okay?
>> Let you down how?
>> Just stick with us.
As long as we all stick
together, you know, if we merge,
we basically sacrificed one of
our old tribe mates for you.
>> We'll see how it goes.
Hopefully...
>> I mean, like, honestly, like,
I like you.
Like, I think, like... I think
you've been a huge, like,
competitor in this game, and,
like, I'm one of those people,
like, I would rather see you go
further just because I really do
think you deserve it.
I really like James personally.
I do-- whether he's a really
good con man or he is exactly
how he puts himself out to be.
From what I've seen so far, my
gut instinct is to trust James.
>> I was kidnapped, so, you
know, I got the clue for the
idols.
I wasn't going to do like Todd
did and be impatient.
There are so many times when
you're by yourself.
I picked off one.
It was the wrong one.
It was a blank sheet of wood.
So I hurried and picked off the
second one.
I kind of had to hustle off to
my bag and hide it.
Did y'all get anything?
>> We didn't rack up, but we got
a decent amount.
>> So I have it now.
I have it in my position, and I
have the two idols.
That's funny.
I'm on Survivor with two idols.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes, it is.
>> This morning, I slept in.
I was in a good mood.
And Courtney comes up and sits
down, and she's like
( sighing ).
We all kind of look at her like,
"Uh, are you okay, Courtney?"
>> Jean-Robert could have gone
last night.
>> What?
>> He could have gone last
night.
>> From the way that I'm playing
the game, I need him.
>> Okay.
>> From the way you're playing
the game, you didn't.
>> But, like, when I make a
point to you guys that, like,
this guy does not like me, he's
not nice to me, and I don't feel
like you stick up for me, I feel
like you play, like, "Okay,
well, we need him, so da, da,
da, da," I can't go along with
that.
>> I don't realize that I do
that, Courtney, and I would love
to stand up for you.
>> You don't have to even
stand... just, like, don't
pander to him and say, "You have
a point, Jean-Robert."
>> You have your opinion about
him.
You don't have to like him.
>> But I don't say anything to
him.
>> I know you don't.
>> But he walks around falling
around like he's the god
everything, and you guys are all
like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
>> We can't have him know that
we don't like him, Courtney.
We can't, or else he will swap
on us.
>> He's not here.
You can say something to me.
Like, the three of you can...
>> Courtney, you are right.
>> All right.
You know...
>> It does worry me that
Courtney will continue to vote
for Jean-Robert every single
time, because all the other
tribe, if there is a merge,
needs to know that one person is
voting against Jean-Robert, and
they will automatically have
Jaime, Peih-Gee, and Erik with
Courtney voting against Jean-
Robert, and that's a campaign to
get him off, which is losing one
of our numbers.
Can we patch things up between
us instead of having hard
feelings like that?
>> What difference does it make?
>> It makes a big difference,
Courtney.
>> What does she want?
Like, what does she expect from
me?
Right now I need my numbers, and
Jean-Robert is one of my
numbers.
Deal with it, bitch.
>> This used to be hanging on
the archway, and it looks like
someone took it off.
I don't know if it was James,
because James now knows that
there's a hidden immunity idol
as well.
I don't know if he knows where
it is or what it is, but you
know, it looks idol-ish.
Peih-Gee didn't really think
much of it.
She doesn't know there's a
hidden idol yet.
So Peih-Gee left.
I just was like, "Well, I guess
I'll grab it," and put it in my
bag.
>> It could definitely say,
like, "Immunity idol" in
Chinese, and I'd have no idea.
It's a weird symbol, so I don't
know what it stands for.
I just want to look in his bag.
Do you think he'll see me if I
pull it out?
I knew it.
He has one in here.
Hey, you watch over there.
Make sure they're not coming
back.
Peih-Gee and James went off to
go frog hunting, so I saw
James'
bag sitting there, and I figured
it might be a good idea to look
through it, because we know
James would have had a good idea
where the hidden immunity idol
was.
I think it's the same thing we
have.
Look.
He's got... he's got one in his
pant leg.
>> He's got two?
>> Yeah.
He has two of them.
>> The first board where the
immunity idol could have been
was a blank board.
Apparently it's missing, because
I didn't see it.
I know that an animal didn't
come up and pick it up and take
it away.
The other one's filled.
Does it some more water?
>> I'll bring it over.
Let's see.
>> I figured Jaime would have
been looking for it, but there's
no way this dummy grabbed the
wrong one, because it would have
to say "Immunity" something on
it.
The thought of this woman having
a blank one, I would not be able
to take it.
I would pass out in pure joy.
My head would explode.
I mean, please, let that happen,
please.
That would be the best thing
ever.
That would be the best... that
would be the best one ever, if
she pulled out a blank thing and
was like... "What do you mean?
But it don't have no writing on
there.
You at least have to have
some... one of these!"
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Zhan Hu getting your first look
at the new Fei Long tribe.
Sherea voted out at the last
tribal council.
Guys ready to get to it?
>> Yes.
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: One of the major
tenets in The Art of War is to
know not only yourself, but to
know your opponent.
Drop your buffs.
You are merged.
>> Oh, my God!
>> What?
>> Hi.
>> All right, one big happy
family.
>> Hi, how are you?
>> We have merged.
So it's pretty exciting.
I really don't know how to take
it all in right now.
It happened so fast.
You know, we just have such a
wide variety of people, so it's
a pretty scary point in the
game.
So I'm excited to have the
hidden immunity idol.
That's going to be a whole new
ball game.
>> We made the merge, huh?
>> PROBST: New buffs.
( cheering )
>> Oh, my God!
Oh, black, you guys!
>> Ninja buffs!
>> PROBST: Reach into the pot.
Frosti, Todd.
>> Oh, my God, they smell good.
>> Oh, they smell so good!
>> These are awesome!
>> PROBST: Go ahead and put them
on, get the new look going.
>> I love them.
>> PROBST: All right, in keeping
with The Art of War, Fei Long,
since thus far you have won the
battle, you will keep your
beach.
In addition, when you get back
to camp, you will find a flag,
paint, and a new boat.
You'll come up with a tribe
name, paint up a new flag.
>> Sweet.
>> PROBST: To celebrate the
merge, you will now enjoy a
merge feast.
>> Yeah!
( cheering and applause )
>> PROBST: In addition to the
feast, you will enjoy an
afternoon of Chinese cultural
performances.
>> Cool!
>> PROBST: All right, now I give
you this strong reminder.
As you head out this afternoon,
keep in mind this game never
stops.
Keep that in mind as you enjoy
this afternoon.
Head out.
Follow the bridge to the
entrance.
( cheering )
Have a good time.
>> Jeff told the group we're
getting to enjoy a feast.
At the same time, there was a
little caution: "The game never
ends."
I was trying to decide what
exactly is he trying to say
right here?-- you know, the game
never ends.
I put a little thought into it,
but I was just so excited to be
eating.
Honestly, I just couldn't wait
till the first course.
( firecrackers popping )
>> Whoo!
Yeah, baby!
>> Oh, my God.
We go in, and we sit down at a
table.
I was pretty pumped, because boo
challenges, yay feast.
>> Look how many dips there are.
>> Sweet and sour pork, you
guys.
>> Beef.
>> They brought in five
vegetarian dishes and five meat
dishes.
And we also got several choices
of alcoholic beverage, which I
enjoyed.
I thought it was quite nice.
>> Congratulations, you guys, on
making it to the top ten.
>> Yeah, everybody,
congratulations.
This is great.
( cheering )
>> Shoot them up.
>> Yeah, girls!
>> Whoo!
>> We had a Chinese acrobat
show, which was amazing.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Those people were so
talented.
It was just so cool to sit there
and drink and watch a great
show.
>> Whoa-- easy!
( applause )
>> We got to see girls doing
cool stuff with plates, girls
twist their bodies into stuff
I've never seen before.
>> Oh, my goodness!
Oh, wow.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Wow.
That's a push-up.
>> I can do that.
>> All in all, it was just
amazing.
We were all just sitting there
like, "Are they really doing
that right now?"
It was so cool.
( firecrackers popping )
>> The first thing I thought
when we merged was "Who are we
going to pick off next?"
>> Wow, girls, you had me at
"Hello."
>> Because even though we're one
tribe now, it's still two
tribes, and we will continue to
be that way until all the Zhan
Hu members are completely gone.
( firecrackers popping )
>> Oh, my lord!
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Whoo!
>> That's our shelter.
>> A lot smaller.
>> It does not keep anything
warm or dry.
>> Your shelter sucks!
>> A great shelter.
>> That means your shelter
sucks!
>> No, our shelter is awesome.
>> This is your shelter.
>> Oh, it looks so much better
than I even thought, though.
>> The merge doesn't change my
game plan at all.
Basically, the members of Zhan
Hu, they're going to go whether
we're merged or not.
>> I want to try this baby out.
>> I do like my position now.
The merge has gotten everybody
into this, like, new tone, like
we've just gotten to this new
level of the game.
And to be honest with you, even
though my name was on ballots at
the first two tribal councils
that I was at, I really don't
see my name being on a ballot at
the next council.
>> Yeah.
>> Hungry monkeys.
>> I feel like hungry monkeys.
>> Angry monkeys.
How about angry monkeys?
>> Something to represent black
buffs, you know?
>> "Black" is "hei" in Chinese.
>> We can be "Black" something
or other.
We can't be "Black," because
then as soon as James is gone,
we'll have to change the name.
>> That did not just come out of
your mouth.
>> Oh, my god.
( Jean-Robert laughing )
>> I'm going to stay here.
I'll be all right.
>> Whatever.
I was on the yellow team.
They put Peih-Gee... they put
Peih-Gee and me on the yellow
team.
( laughter )
>> We were on the yellow team.
>> I do like the idea of "Black"
something.
I do... I really do like the
idea of "Black" something.
>> Monsoon survivors.
>> I like it.
I like "Black Monsoon," because
we're here during monsoon
season.
>> Does anybody know how to say
"monsoon"?
>> "Dei fung."
"Da fung" is "fighting wind."
It is a unifying factor.
>> We got through the wind.
We got through the rain.
I think it's good.
>> It'll literally be "Fighting
Wind."
>> "Fighting Wind."
>> "Black Fighting Wind."
>> Now that we've merged, we are
all playing for individual
immunity.
But there are six original Fei
Long members to four original
Zhan Hu.
The biggest factor is whether I
have James and whether I have
Frosti.
If I can get them both with me
on these first two votes...
these first two votes are
crucial for me to know whether
I'm going to be in a powerful
position or a really sucky
position.
>> It is Jeff!
>> Jeff's here.
Guys, guys, you got a visitor.
>> PROBST: No welcome?
>> Jeff's here!
>> Hey, Jeff!
( applause )
>> Hey, guys, guys, Jeff's here!
>> Jeff's at our camp!
>> Is anyone listening?
>> Nobody cares?
>> PROBST: What up?
>> Welcome!
>> Hey, Jeff!
>> Hi!
>> PROBST: Working on the new
flag?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Nice.
What's the tribe name?
>> Hei Da Fung.
>> "Black Fighting Wind."
>> PROBST: "Black Fighting
Wind," Hei Da Fung.
>> Hei Da Fung.
>> PROBST: Well, I brought you a
little something.
>> We love a little something.
>> We love everything.
>> Is it cookies?
>> PROBST: It's not cookies.
>> Pizza!
>> PROBST: It's not pizza.
It's something much better than
food.
It is a gift for one of you.
It is the individual immunity
necklace.
>> Wow!
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: And I brought it
because it is time for our first
individual immunity challenge.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Follow me.
>> PROBST: Plop a seat wherever
you like.
So before the merge celebration,
I said, "Let me issue one
reminder: the game never stops."
And I suggested you keep it in
mind as you enjoyed the
festivities.
For today's challenge, you will
be tested on your recollection
of events that happened during
the feast and the celebration.
You'll have a tablet.
You'll write your answer down.
If you're wrong, you're out--
single elimination, no second
chances.
>> PROBST: Last person left
standing wins individual
immunity, is safe at the next
tribal council.
For the other nine, somebody
will be going home.
>> I'm so screwed.
>> PROBST: You say you're
screwed?
Why, Frosti?
>> I have a horrible memory.
>> PROBST: Going into this
challenge, who is ready for it?
Anybody here pay particular
attention?
>> I paid particular attention
to how much I could eat.
>> PROBST: You guys ready for
the first question?
Here we go, first question: how
many times during the
celebration did firecrackers go
off?
Nothing subtle about the
firecrackers when they went off.
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer is three.
There's one at the beginning,
one during, and one at the end
of the feast.
James got it wrong.
Amanda got it wrong.
Courtney got it wrong.
And Peih-Gee got it wrong.
You are all out of the
challenge.
Todd got it right.
Frosti, Jaime, Jean-Robert got
it right.
And Denise and Erik got it
right.
We are down to six.
What was the centerpiece on the
table?
Describe it.
Tell me what it was.
Everybody reveal.
Todd says a dragon.
Frosti, Jaime, Jean-Robert all
say a dragon.
Denise says a dragon.
And Erik says a slender, dark,
glass container...
>> "Slender dark glass
container-- soy sauce?-- and a
stone dragon."
>> PROBST: So you covered the
whole table.
It's a good thing you did.
The last thing was right.
Dragon is correct.
Everybody got it right.
Next question: there was a tall
pole with knife blades as ladder
rungs in the middle of the
courtyard.
What color was the pole?
One long, tall pole situated in
the middle of the courtyard--
what color was the pole?
All right, everybody reveal.
Todd originally wrote yellow.
He changed it to red.
Frosti and Jaime say yellow.
Jean-Robert said red.
Denise said red.
Erik said red.
Correct answer was yellow.
>> There we go!
>> PROBST: Todd is out.
Jean-Robert is out.
And Denise and Erik are out.
We are down to Frosti and Jaime.
If one of you misses and the
other gets it right, that person
wins individual immunity.
Next question, immunity on the
line: the four cultural dancers
with the long, flowing skirts
wore what on their feet?
The four cultural dancers, they
had the long, flowing skirts.
What did they wear on their
feet?
>> This is not fair, because I
was not looking at their feet.
>> PROBST: All right, reveal.
Jaime says silk stockings.
Frosti says nothing.
The correct answer is...
nothing.
Frosti wins first individual
immunity.
>> Wow, Frosti.
( applause )
>> PROBST: Come on over.
Turn around, brother.
Congratulations.
You're safe at the next tribal
council, guaranteed a one in
nine shot at a million bucks.
For the rest of you, somebody
will be going home.
For once, you don't have to go
back to camp.
You're already here.
I'll split.
I'll see you at tribal council.
Congratulations.
>> Damn.
From now on, we got to go to
every tribal.
>> Huh?
>> Now we have to go to every
tribal.
The predicament today is that
there's tribal council.
There's a big chance that it's
going to be me, Jaime, or Erik
that's going home, since Frosti
has immunity.
And the big question mark is do
we have James's vote?
And we don't know if James is on
our side.
>> Huh?
Uh-huh.
>> This is a huge vote for us
tonight, because we will know
where everybody's loyalties
stands.
I mean, it's going to be really
interesting.
>> How great would that be?
You've got them both though?
>> Yeah.
>> Five, right?
Me, you, Amanda, Denise,
Courtney.
>> Yeah.
>> Beautiful.
>> Please hold that together.
>> I promise to.
I'll shake on it.
>> I mean, you know I can't talk
to you that much, especially
right now, but I just had to
tell somebody.
>> We just have to keep loyal.
We can't let Jaime and Peih-Gee
and Erik break us up.
>> No.
>> I don't think Erik will.
Jaime is a silent leader of the
old Zhan Hu Tribe, definitely.
She's really close with Erik,
and by getting rid of Jaime,
it'll break up that alliance.
And Peih-Gee you can just kind
of see through, you know.
She's a little devious.
But Jaime is so threatening
because people don't see that
right away with Jaime.
Denise is in for sure.
Me, you, like, are locked in.
Todd is locked in now.
But Courtney kind of has a mind
of her own.
Courtney said at tribal council
she doesn't have anyone here she
likes except Sherea.
She was saying stuff like that.
She like, "Well, you guys keep
voting off everyone I like.
You voted off Leslie.
You want to vote out Sherea."
I'm like, "Courtney, this is a
game."
>> Well, the problem is Courtney
keeps getting close to people
that we can't have here.
>> I mean, we've done everything
so good.
>> I know, I know.
>> We've got to watch Courtney
because she is a loose cannon.
She does stray off and fall in
love with any swinging Dick or
Harry that floats and smiles at
her.
But damn, you don't get friends
on Survivor.
This ain't Love Connection.
Ain't nobody trying to get a
match or a relationship.
You're supposed to make the
strongest team you can and align
with some people you somewhat
can trust to win a million
dollars and stop playing around!
>> Thank you.
>> It's good.
We have every vote from here on
out.
>> I know.
>> Okay?
I love it.
It will be you, me, and Amanda.
>> It's perfect.
>> 100%.
>> You know right now it has to
go Jaime, Peih-Gee, Erik.
>> I am going to make a
suggestion, and hear me out on
this.
Everybody on our team already
knows Jaime is shady.
We're already suspicious of her,
and nobody's going to trust her.
Peih-Gee we don't know about
because she's just starting to
work her magic.
>> Right.
>> Like I said.
Today I was, like, surprised.
She just went and plopped her
arm on me.
I was like, "You know what?
That's kind of cool.
That's kind of cool."
I was like, "That's kind of
cool.
This girl's kind of cool.
This girl's all right."
I don't want her to feel all
right.
>> And she's working her way
with Courtney.
>> I don't want to feel all
right with her in a few days.
>> Right.
>> You know?
>> So...
>> Oh, one thing also.
If somehow you do end up
screwing me over, you know, the
game or whatever-- and I don't
believe that's going to happen,
but if I get screwed, I'm going
to hold you responsible, not
Amanda.
>> Okay.
>> Just so you know.
And you will never, ever see a
juror lobby so hard against
somebody.
You will not win.
>> Okay, okay.
>> If I get screwed, it's going
to be on you, because I know you
have more power than her.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
It's the three of us.
We're going.
>> Good.
>> If I didn't agree to all of
his terms, right away the trust
with me and him, he wouldn't
trust me anymore, so he would
have moved along and found
another alliance and done who
knows what.
So of course I agreed to it all
and was like "Yeah, we're going
to the top three, man.
We're going all the way.
I'm watching your back."
Little does Jean-Robert know...
like, little clue, no, he has no
idea that I'm ready to... when I
need to.
>> I have no idea.
Some days I do.
Some days I don't.
>> Uh-huh, I'm sure they will.
>> Did she?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, hello.
>> Me and Erik found it, and he
has it in his pack.
>> Wait.
>> Okay, this... I'll...
>> How do you know it's the
immunity idol?
>> Because there's two sides to
the sign, right?
We were lying there.
One day I was on the bed, and it
was just lying on the floor.
So I picked it up, and I was
like, "Erik, what is it?"
We're like, "I don't know."
So he put it in his bag.
Well, then the next day, we
found two of them in James's
bag.
So we're like, "He must have got
spooked by us and dropped it."
And we picked it up and put it
in our possession.
We're thinking we'll play it
tonight anyway, no matter what.
>> Uh-huh.
>> If they're all voting for me,
and I have the idol, then the
only votes that count are ours,
so Jean-Robert will be voted out
instead.
So we might as well try and use
it tonight.
>> Jaime came up to me with Erik
and said that she had found
something that she thought was
an idol.
Now, I've seen the actual idol
from the Fei Long camp.
And what she's describing is
similar, so there is a
possibility that she has one.
The worst that would happen
would be that Jean-Robert would
end up going home if she knew to
play it.
And now that I've won the
immunity idol, I'm in a safe
place, and both tribes think
that I'm with them.
So I could easily be considered
a swing vote, and I could go
either way.
>> What are you thinking?
>> Do you know anything about
the immunity idol over here?
>> Well, I know a little, but
not much.
>> Okay.
If you can somehow just keep me
here tonight, I think I know who
has your immunity idol, and I
know who has mine.
>> Do you know who has them
both?
>> I do.
>> Okay.
>> And I'll tell you tomorrow if
you can keep me around.
>> And you know, I acted all
interested when Jaime told me
that she knew who had the hidden
immunity idols and that she was
going to tell me, but she made
it sound like someone from their
tribe has one and someone from
our tribe has one.
Wow, does she have to catch up.
So... she's... she's on the
small bike in the back, you
know, just pedaling as fast as
she can.
How did you find out who got
ours?
>> Um, long story.
I'll explain it, everything,
but...
>> Okay, okay.
>> I've come to realize that I'm
very good at playing stupid, and
it works to my advantage, so I
think I'm just going to stick on
with it.
As far as the other tribe's
concerned, I think they kind of
think I'm little Jessica Simpson
out here running around in the
jungle.
If Todd sees me play the hidden
immunity idol tonight, he's
definitely going to be floored
when he sees it come out.
I think it's probably going to
shock everyone, including Jeff.
I'm not as dumb as I look, and
maybe they're figuring it out.
>> Dude, I'm telling you, it has
to go Peih-Gee and then Jaime.
>> I don't want any dissension
amongst us until we get to the
final six, until all of them are
gone.
Then we can act as much as a
fool as we want.
>> It's Peih-Gee.
>> We can't screw this up.
>> I'm telling you it's done.
>> There should be no mistaking.
>> I'm just telling you 100%,
that's where I'm going.
>> No, don't say that.
We're going to pick who it is,
and we're sticking together.
>> It's Peih-Gee.
Okay, yes, we are.
>> Jean-Robert probably would go
home tonight, because Jean-
Robert is stupid.
>> This girl is the enemy.
This girl is the devil!
>> The best scenario is for the
Fei Long Tribe to stick together
and vote off the Zhan Hu Tribe,
but Jean-Robert's dumb ass is
going to vote for Peih-Gee, even
though we all said Jaime.
It's been Jaime for a month now.
The Zhan Hu people naturally are
going to vote for Jean-Robert.
They know he's the easy win.
And lord help him if Courtney's
dumb ass decides to vote for
Jean-Robert out of pure spite
because she just wants to be
hateful.
>> PROBST: Full house.
Amanda, from a game point of
view, how did the merge change
the game?
>> Well, Jeff, it's kind of
nice, actually, because we spent
a lot of time as, like, Fei
Long, wondering what the other
tribe was doing.
So it's kind of nice to have
some new people around, and we
all get along really well.
We're having a lot of fun.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, when you
hear Amanda say it's fun, does
that make you think she has no
clue what this game is about or
that she's extremely confident
that she's not going anywhere?
>> Well, of course, I mean, they
have higher numbers.
So I'm sure it's easier for them
to have fun.
>> PROBST: Jean-Robert, you're a
student of people.
Have you noticed a shift in how
people are operating?
>> It's so interesting how the
dynamic changed from the team
now to the individual.
Now that we're in the individual
situation, I very much see
Courtney making it down to the
bottom two, bottom three,
because she's not going to be
perceived as the type of threat
that James or myself might be.
So now she's somebody that
nobody's going to be gunning for
for a while.
I don't see her name showing up
on a ballot for a long time.
>> PROBST: Courtney, you're
rolling your eyes.
Why?
>> Because this is now Jean-
Robert trying to be like, "The
biggest threat in the room is
the little blonde!
Come on, everyone!"
It's a person who I don't get
along with pointing out that all
of a sudden I'm going to be the
biggest threat there is.
It's just... it's funny.
>> I didn't say she's going to
be the biggest threat.
I said that it's likely she's
going to get the furthest.
>> Which translates to "You're a
big threat."
>> I don't think it does.
It means that you're not a
threat.
And the same is true for several
people in this group.
>> PROBST: James, why does that
bother you?
>> Jean-Robert, he just don't be
quiet.
I don't know.
He just don't stop.
>> PROBST: And you think that
that might become a liability?
>> Yeah, he puts his name on the
chopping block because he's
always saying, "Oh, well, I'm
going on the chopping block
today."
He'll mention it every day.
When he's tired, he'll announce
that he's tired.
He doesn't have to do that.
See, when you're tired, just go
lay down.
We understand.
You're a card player.
You haven't been in the sun.
You're used to people bringing
the food up to you, probably
putting it in your mouth and
helping you chew.
You know, we don't expect that
much from you.
So you don't have to go on and
on about it, which I guess is
part of his tactic.
But I'm like, "Dude, you don't
have to talk that much."
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, when you
guys all merged together, did
you try to find cracks in the
Fei Long group?
>> You kind of know about some
of the cracks already.
We've had spies back and forth.
I know Jean-Robert's name has
come up quite a bit.
He's politicking his ass off.
He's doing everything he can to
ensure that he's got as many
votes on the jury as possible.
>> PROBST: Jaime, what do you
think the key is to getting the
attention off you?
If you hear that your name is on
the block, what should you do?
>> You know, I just kind of
wanted to come in here and talk
to the Fei Long members, just in
case there was a crack, just in
case there was someone on that
team that they just can't stand
enough that they would be happy
to get rid of.
You know, it just would take one
other person to be like, "I
really can't stand this person
anymore; I want them to go home,
and Jaime is more pleasant to be
around, so..."
>> PROBST: All right, Frosti has
the immunity necklace.
I know you're not giving it up.
You cannot vote for Frosti.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Erik, you're up.
>> Trying to keep it Zhan Hu.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
>> Jeff, I have a question for
you.
>> PROBST: Yes.
>> I found this at camp lying on
the floor, so I thought it might
be immunity.
>> PROBST: Thanks.
The rules of Survivor state that
if the hidden immunity idol is
played, any votes cast against
that person will not count, and
the person with the next highest
number of votes be will be sent
home.
That's in the case of a hidden
immunity idol being played.
This, however, is not a hidden
immunity idol.
>> Oh, my gosh!
( laughter )
Oh, oh!
>> PROBST: Any votes cast
against Jaime will count.
I'll now read the votes.
First vote, Jean-Robert.
Jaime.
Two votes Jaime, one vote Jean-
Robert.
Jean-Robert.
We're tied, two votes Jaime, two
votes Jean-Robert.
Jean-Robert.
That's three votes Jean-Robert,
two votes Jaime.
Jaime.
Tied again, three votes Jaime,
three votes Jean-Robert.
Jaime.
Four votes Jaime, three votes
Jean-Robert.
Jaime.
That's five votes Jaime, three
votes Jean-Robert.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: China and the first
member of our jury, Jaime.
That's six.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Jaime, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, the game has just shifted
again.
With Jaime becoming the first
member of the jury, you are now
voting people out of the game
who will ultimately decide who
they feel is most deserving of
the title of sole survivor and
the million dollars that goes
with it.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> I would love to see some
craziness.
>> PROBST: ...Todd wants to
blindside James.
>> If we blindside him, both
immunities would be out of play.
>> PROBST: ...causing his
alliance to question his
leadership.
>> Todd is all over the place
right now.
>> He won't listen to anyone.
>> PROBST: And Peih-Gee makes a
power play.
>> There's five of us here.
I'll try anything at this point.
>> I learned that I'm probably
too nice for the game of
Survivor.
I wish Erik and Peih-Gee the
best of luck.
I made a bad decision with
James.
He's obviously not very
trustworthy, and I hate that I
trusted him.
I'm kicking myself in the butt
right now.
I tried to plain the hidden
immunity idol.
It wasn't it, but it was worth a
shot, so I'm glad I tried it.