>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor...
>> Getting past last night's
vote was big.
>> JEFF: Jean-Robert narrowly
escaped the vote.
>> But at he next tribal council
I'm not that worried, because
Courtney is always the weak link
in every challenge, and if she
survives the next tribal council
she's got to be the luckiest
girl in Survivor history.
>> I would prefer if Jean-Robert
goes next because he's just so
unpleasant.
He's, like, a cocky son of a
bitch.
And he sucks so bad.
There's no getting out of that.
>> JEFF: At Zhan Hu...
>> I don't know, man, find
something, think of something.
>> JEFF: ...Dave continued to
rub people the wrong way.
>> Thanks for listening.
>> The same way you do with
everybody else.
You just listen, listen, listen,
right?
>> Dave's put himself in a weird
position with everybody.
I mean, he does help around
camp, but he's also pissing
people off.
>> JEFF: And Sherea conserved
her energy around camp for the
challenges.
>> I'm getting frustrated
because Sherea is trying to get
away with not helping out.
>> I'm going ride the workhorse
until the tails fall off,
because I'm not doing anything
until I have to.
>> JEFF: At the immunity
challenge...
Sherea launches again and
scores!
Sherea rose to the occasion.
But James once again dominated.
James connects again!
Leading Fei Long to victory.
Nobody going home from Fei Long.
Back at the Zhan Hu camp, both
Dave and Sherea were clearly in
trouble.
>> I think if it were to me, you
know, if we could get rid of
both of them, it would be great.
>> JEFF: But at tribal council,
Sherea convinced the tribe of
her value.
>> If we don't save our energy
for challenges, we'll never get
further ahead in the game.
>> JEFF: And Dave paid the price
for his abrasive personality.
Fourth person voted out
of Survivor: China, Dave.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> Oh, we slept in.
>> With Dave out of the picture,
everybody's just kind of
peaceful, just chilling.
You know, we sleep late and
then we have a lot of
relaxation time.
>> You okay?
>> Losing is so boring, because
we've already done it so much.
I want to do something
different.
We should have a really strong
team now.
But the problem is Fei Long,
they also have a very strong
team.
They're well led by Aaron.
They've got the strongest
player, James, and some very
intelligent people.
So they're a hard team to beat.
>> I think as long as, like, we,
all, like, work together, like,
equally in every aspect, that
way we're all strong here.
We're all strong at challenges.
It sounds like that's what that
other tribe is doing.
I mean, it helps that they have
James, but...
>> I definitely feel like the
outsider in the tribe just
because the four of them kind of
clique up sometimes.
So I want to spice things up.
I want some drama or something
going on.
I'm really looking for forward
to something changing.
>> I wouldn't mind going by
Taylor.
>> That's a cool name.
>> I like Taylor.
>> I have a friend named Taylor.
>> Really?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Jaime and are kind of in the
Garden of Eden setting, minus
all the fruit.
It's biblical in the sense that
there's man and woman and we
like hanging out.
What's yours?
>> Nicole.
>> Jaime Nicole Dugan.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That's a nice little sweet,
Southern name.
>> Yep.
Erik and I have known each
other, like... I guess it's 13
days now.
I don't know what's wrong with
him.
I can't find anything wrong with
him so far.
He's really attractive.
>> I like you a lot, so...
>> All right.
>> I just want to get my
thoughts out, just to know that
I've said it.
I don't know.
I just... I'm a virgin.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
A few years ago I was like, "I'm
not ready."
And I said it was because I was
too young, but it was really
because I think I wasn't finding
the right person.
>> I think it's great that Erik
is still a virgin, you know.
I think it does prove that he's
even more trustworthy than I
even thought before.
So I'm trying to make it with
him all the way through.
>> Yeah.
The new word on the street is
that there's an immunity idol,
and Jaime wants to entrust me
with the information.
That's going to hopefully help
in the game.
I don't know what's going to
happen with Jaime and I's
relationship, but she seems like
a good all-around person to be
aligned with right now at this
stage of the game.
>> It's going to be another hot
one, guys.
>> Another glorious morning here
in China.
>> I am carrying most of the
tribe's weight as far as work
and the challenges, but Denise
really does bust her ass out
here.
She's the other one that really
pulls the rope around here.
I mean, you can't beat that.
I like women like her.
She's a strong, good woman.
She's there to complement you
and work with you.
That's attractive.
I like that.
If Denise was ten years younger
or if I was older, whichever
way, Denise would be in trouble.
Yeah.
Damn, that's enough to eat.
>> We should have brought a
bucket and filled it up with
some water.
Right now the person I trust
most is James.
Him and I get along very well.
>> You think this rice will
work?
They like rice.
>> He picked up on my work
ethic.
I've picked up on his.
Him and I seem to have a little
connection going.
>> I can trust him and know I
can stick with him and ride his
coattail as Long as I can.
>> James, how is our breakfast
coming along, boss?
You're the cook.
You cook, and we eat.
>> Someone's coming in.
>> Oh, no, you guys.
Something's going on.
>> Ni hao.
>> Thank you.
>> Hello, hi.
>> Is that for us?
>> Hi, thank you.
>> Hello.
>> Hi.
We have a message, guys.
Should we read it?
Uh-oh, hold on, hold on.
Okay.
"Fei Long, choose the two
warriors from Zhan Hu who you
feel could best help strengthen
your tribe, win challenges and
avoid tribal council.
Circle their names below.
This fisherman will get your new
tribe members and bring them
back to your camp."
>> Oh, my god.
>> Well, what's the catch?
>> Well, the catch will probably
be that they get to pick two of
ours, and they're going to pick,
obviously, like, you and James,
Aaron.
>> But, I mean, it's not about
strength all the time.
>> It pretty much is about
strength.
>> I think someone's going to
get switched for sure on our
tribe.
I think that they're probably
going to have a note quite
similar that says, you know,
"Circle two people from the
other tribe that you think will
benefit yours, and they are now
part of your tribe."
I don't know.
But the situation at camp right
now is we have to pick two
members from the other tribe.
>> Okay.
Do you want to have just have
everyone have just who their
number one pick would be?
>> Frosti.
>> I'd say Frosti.
>> Okay, Frosti is the number
one pick.
>> Do you think it's Frosti and
Sherea?
>> I think that's a smart move.
>> All right, do it up.
>> Okay, fine.
>> Frosti and Sherea.
>> All right.
>> We think that Frosti and
Sherea will benefit our camp
because they're both tough,
they're both strong and fast,
and, you know, they seem like
good people.
But it's kind of crazy.
It's almost like everything
you've devised has to be put on
pause for a few minutes while
you figure new things out.
>> James, if they get the same
note, they are 100% picking you.
>> "Zhan Hu, choose the two
warriors from Fei Long who you
think can best help to
strengthen your tribe.
Circle their names below.
This fisherman will go get your
new tribe members and bring them
back to your camp."
>> So we're getting two
people.
That means we'll have, what,
seven?
>> We'll have seven.
That is the craziest thing I
have ever heard.
>> That is messed up.
>> Oh, my god, they're going to
be so pissed.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my god, now Zhan Hu is
going to have seven and Fei Long
is going to have five.
I mean, it's crazy.
It's going to really cripple the
other tribe.
I mean, it's huge.
Power really shifted to our
tribe today with that crazy
twist.
>> James.
I call James.
>> James is number one.
We all call James?
>> James.
>> Please.
>> So none of the women.
We don't want any of the women.
>> I think we should get Aaron
and vote him off.
That would be kind of dirty,
but...
>> Yeah, if we got Aaron then we
would be able to vote him out.
>> We could just vote him off.
If we lose he would be the first
one to go and we don't have to
worry about us.
>> I'm ready to do it.
Let's do it.
>> Aaron?
>> Go.
>> James and Aaron.
Let's flip it around.
>> Come on, guys.
Zhan Hu!
>> Zhan Hu and Fei Long just
flipped.
We're now seven-five instead of
five-seven.
And we have a huge advantage.
We have all the strongest
players.
So it's looking really good for
us.
>> All right, come on, guys.
Zhan Hu!
>> Here they come.
>> Is it them?
Should we go down and welcome
them?
>> Yes.
>> Are they waving?
>> No.
>> I'm waving, though.
>> They're pissed.
They're totally pissed that we
picked them.
>> Is that them standing?
>> No, I don't see anybody
standing.
They're probably sitting down.
>> This is so weird.
>> What?
>> Oh!
>> Apparently that wasn't the
end of the twist.
Seems Fei Long picked two people
from Zhan Hu, and those people
were Sherea and myself.
>> Oh, my god.
>> I don't even know what to
say.
>> I don't, either.
>> What are we going to do?
>> It never crossed my mind that
they were going to take two of
us.
We were just like, "Oh, we get
to have two strong people."
We didn't think about it at all.
That was really dumb.
>> Whatever we're going to do,
we're just going to do our best
to stay in it, you know.
No matter what happens, you guys
have control of the two biggest
players in the game, so remember
that.
>> So use it to your advantage.
>> I'll miss you.
>> I'll miss you, too.
>> See you soon.
>> Bye, guys.
New adventure.
>> Yep.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> Yeah.
>> These are different drivers,
you guys.
They're here to get two of us.
>> Yep.
>> Ni hau.
>> Okay, here we go.
>> Thank you.
It says, "Fei Long, if it is
your name that is circled, pack
your personal belongings and go
with this fisherman to join your
new tribe at Zhan Hu."
Aaron, James.
>> They have a pretty sweet team
now.
>> What are we going to do
without you people?
without you?
>> We've got a great camp, we've
got such great momentum, and
we've been such a great force on
this team, and now we're
switching and everything is
messed up.
>> I can't stand it, losing our
two strongest warriors.
>> I thought you were our
strongest warrior, big boy.
>> Yeah, you're Jean-Robert.
Yeah.
>> Bye, Amanda.
>> Bye.
>> Bye, Todd.
>> Take care.
Be good.
>> Man, I just fixed my part of
the bed.
I don't have any ties, anything
with Aaron.
Going over to Zhan Hu, I'm
pretty much by myself now.
I'm starting all over again.
I'm going to have to work my way
into the system again.
>> We're giving up our two
strongest warriors, Aaron and
James.
If that's not bad enough, James
is one of my strongest allies in
this whole game.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Bye-bye.
>> I was a little upset.
I mean, I've been getting along
with James.
James works around here.
But, you know, I mean, things
change.
Things change for the good,
things change for the bad.
>> That means that Jean-Robert
is going to have to actually
move his ass and get water.
>> We should probably talk
about, before those guys get
here, what our plan is going to
be.
>> I say we don't even think
about it until we lose.
>> I agree.
>> No, I say we have to think
about it, because it's not
something we can talk about when
they're here.
If it came down to it, at first
tribal council we go for Sherea
and then we go for Frosti.
>> Totally.
>> Sounds good to me.
>> The popular thing would be,
"Well, you know, Jean-Robert,
yeah, yeah, yeah..."
>> Why do you say that's the
popular thing, Jean-Robert?
>> I'm just saying that...
>> No, really, Sherea is..
>> I know that you guys are
smart players and everything.
I'm just saying that...
>> Right now we get rid of them.
>> Right now, I think that's the
important thing.
>> Todd and Courtney and Amanda,
who knows?
They may just decide, "Let's get
rid of Jean-Robert."
Today is a terrible day for Fei
Long, and today is a god-awful
day for Jean-Robert.
>> James and I are going to Zhan
Hu.
We just switched tribes.
And I'm ready.
>> We're going to have to make
this work, dude.
>> We're going to be fine, dude.
>> I'm chillin'.
>> We're cool.
We're going in with only two
people, you know, and they have
three.
So it is a cause for, like, some
apprehension on my part.
Where is their hut?
>> Here they are.
Ahoy.
>> Good to have you guys.
>> Who knew?
>> Good to see you.
Welcome.
>> What are you guys, swimming?
>> Give me a hug.
>> Hi.
>> No way!
>> Yes!
>> My god!
>> We have alcohol!
>> When Aaron and James came
over, they brought a little
bounty with them.
It was a big basket full of
different fruits and nuts.
>> Did y'all think it was going
to be you two?
>> We knew it was going to be
James.
( laughter )
We didn't know who else it would
be.
>> Zhan Hu is going to be a
little bit harder.
All my people are over there on
Fei Long.
These people are all happy.
Everything is relaxed.
My people are miserable over
there.
I like misery.
>> Y'all are now yellow.
>> It's crazy seeing you guys
yellow.
>> It's weird, like, y'all are
on our side now.
>> Who is the brain out of the
group?
>> Actually, we all are.
We're all, I mean...
>> We are in different ways,
sort of.
>> Me and her do puzzles for fun
and stuff like that back home.
>> I can do puzzles.
>> Strategy.
>> As far as us three are
concerned, we all are kind of
balanced.
>> Tomorrow y'all really need to
pull this off.
I'll make water, I'll get
everything done, because I'm
used to doing that anyway.
Y'all focus on what y'all need
to do tomorrow to gets things
ready, get yourself focused to
win.
>> Of course James and Aaron
know they're on the chopping
block, so they're definitely
trying to fire us up for winning
the challenges.
>> Make a toast to the new Zhan
Hu.
May we prevail.
We have control over the two
strongest guys right now in the
game.
I mean, it's a major advantage.
It's just what we choose to do
with it.
>> Thank you for welcoming us.
>> Here they come.
>> We've got to stick together
now.
>> All right.
>> Hey, guys.
>> Hello!
>> Hello.
>> Welcome!
>> Welcome to Fei Long.
>> You guys are Skinny Minnie.
>> The fact that Frosti and
Sherea are coming over to our
side is kind of exciting,
because I may be able to get
great bonds with them.
So who knows what I can build
there?
>> It's a basket of food!
( cheering )
>> Let's celebrate, guys!
>> Coming over to Fei Long, I
feel like I'm starting over, you
know, in the game all over
again.
So I'm going to do my best to
try to get to know them and try
to find my place and fit in.
>> Pop open one of those
bottles.
>> Welcome, tribe members.
>> Welcome, you guys.
>> My position at Zhan Hu was
not secure in the fact that I
wasn't the hardest worker at
camp.
So I'm hoping over here that
they kind of see me in a
different light, and maybe I
can, you know, step it up some.
>> We don't have any cooks.
>> I can cook a little
something-something.
>> I'll try and bring back clean
fish, and you can cook
something.
>> I can't believe I'm here.
This place is so different.
>> Really?
>> This is a dangerous place for
me.
Things are really messed up now.
>> I really wanted to see you
guys' camp.
I just didn't know it was going
to be permanent.
I'm out of my comfort zone,
obviously, because I'm
outnumbered by old Fei Long
members with Sherea.
My first goal is to figure out
what's going on around here,
what kind of alliances I can
sense, just see where I can put
myself that's going to keep me
around.
>> Get a little rice going here.
This morning I just felt like
giving us a little bit of a head
start because we lost our sous
chef, Aaron and James.
So I decided to come out here
and just try to build a fire.
And since I got the fire going,
I might as well start getting
the rice going.
>> I know.
Who is going to have to argue
with him now, though?
I don't want to argue with him
anymore.
>> Waking up to everybody
bashing Jean-Robert was better
than the food that we got the
night before.
To me, that just makes me so
much more comfortable knowing
that there's somebody here they
already have problems with.
So it's looking like Jean-Robert
is in a bit of a pinch.
>> I'm going to go check the
traps for shrimp.
I started the rice.
I mean, the rice is basically
done.
>> Jean-Robert woke up early
this morning, which he never
does, and he started cooking
breakfast for everybody.
He's trying to save his butt
right now.
>> Denise, if you want, maybe we
can set out that second net.
>> What's that?
>> I'm not the tribe leader.
I don't want to be tribe leader.
I'm just saying what I want to
do.
>> Huh?
I'm not handing out any orders.
>> Okay.
>> I just asked for help with
the setting out of the net.
>> Thank you.
Sherea can cook.
That's going to be real helpful
for us.
Maybe you can make some sort of,
like, sardine fried rice for
Todd to start out with, and I'll
bring back shrimp, and then you
can make shrimp fried rice.
That would be great.
>> Morning.
>> Morning, everybody.
Welcome to Fei Long.
I love it.
>> Seems like right now, Jean-
Robert is the one that gets on
everybody's nerves.
I definitely believe this could
be the opening for me with the
way they kind of don't get along
with Jean-Robert as great for
everybody.
I'm definitely going to try to
make my way in there.
>> That looked really cool when
you guys pulled up, all, like,
chilling on top of that boat.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, it was beautiful.
We've got a super tribe right
here.
>> Yeah, we do.
>> I mean, there isn't any
reason why we shouldn't win
again and again and again.
>> Yeah.
>> This is Zhan Hu.
This is my new tribe.
Erik and Peih-Gee and Jaime,
they're really awesome people,
you know?
And they're really solid.
>> This is so much fun.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I couldn't imagine a better
way to spend the summer.
I feel comfortable here.
I don't know how James feels,
but we'll see.
>> James is amazingly...
>> He's, like, the powerhouse.
Yeah.
That's why... he's pretty much
the catalyst and why we're
winning these challenges.
You know, the only thing is
that, yes, James is good here.
When we go to the merge, bad.
Yeah.
Everyone has to consider how
great of an athlete that James
is.
You know, and when there is a
merge that comes, you know, how
dangerous he could be if he's
a... what they call an immunity
hog.
All of us are pretty much equal.
James is physically a little bit
more than us.
That is strategy talk.
That was a subtle card I played,
you know, just to save my butt
just in case we do lose an
immunity.
>> Aaron, okay, say we merge and
Jean-Robert is still left, would
he be the first person once we
merged that you'd vote off?
>> Let me think about that.
>> Aaron's smart.
He's athletic, he's good-
looking, which always helps
people like you a little more.
>> I don't know, you know?
>> But I think Aaron is a little
bit crafty.
He's probably holding a little
bit back.
Now that we have Aaron and James
over here, Frosti and Sherea are
over at the other camp.
I don't know how long members of
my original alliance are going
to last over there.
So definitely I'm going to try
to pull Jaime aside and have a
talk with her, see what she
thinks of everything.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
How did you feel, Todd, when
Frosti and Sherea showed up?
>> You know, Frosti and Sherea
are great, so I thought they
were a good asset to our tribe.
I mean, we did lose two strong,
awesome people, but we also
gained two people that I'm sure
are going to fight hard.
>> JEFF: Aaron, is this a good
move for you?
>> It puts us on the chopping
block as new members.
We really have to put up or shut
up right here in this challenge
and make it happen, and win.
If you win, you don't go home.
>> JEFF: Are you guys ready to
get to your first challenge as
new tribes?
>> Yes, sir.
>> JEFF: First things first.
Amanda, give it up.
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: Once again, immunity is
back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, two
members of each tribe will swim
out to a platform.
You will then alternate diving
into a water, where you'll find
a cage filled with 12 disks
representing the signs of the
Chinese zodiac.
To release those disks you have
to remove as many bamboo poles
as possible before resurfacing.
You'll then put all 12 disks in
a boat and swim to shore.
The three remaining tribe
members will then match each
disk to its corresponding spot
on the board by twisting it and
turning it until they lock into
place.
First tribe to finish wins
immunity, safe at least one more
night here in China.
Losers, tribal council, somebody
will be voted out.
Fei Long, you have two extra
members, sitting two people out.
Who's it going to be?
Amanda and Courtney.
Take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to figure out who your
swimmers are going to be, we'll
get started.
Erik and Aaron swimming for Zhan
Hu, Frosti and Jean-Robert for
Fei Long.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Swim, guys.
Swim, swim, swim!
>> JEFF: You need to get as many
sticks out in one breath before
switching out.
Go!
Jean-Robert is in for Fei Long.
Aaron in for Zhan Hu.
Aaron is up.
Jean-Robert is up.
Got to get back to the mat
before the next guy can go.
Go!
The longer you stay under, the
more sticks you can pull out.
>> Go, Jean-Robert!
It broke a little bit of my
heart to say that.
>> JEFF: Both tribes pretty even
at this point.
With each dive it's getting more
and more difficult.
Deepest one's about 12 feet.
Erik really winded.
Getting very hard for people to
breathe.
>> Boys, take your time and just
get your breath first.
Wait a minute.
Wait a long minute.
( laughs )
>> Focus, children.
>> Focus on what?
>> Something.
Focus on thinking of the things
we have to...
>> The puzzle?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Getting down to the
last few sticks.
>> I got one.
>> JEFF: Zhan Hu thinks they
have all 12.
Got to get them in the boat and
drag it to shore.
Frosti down for a long time.
>> Got them all.
Come on, Jean-Robert!
Grab the disks!
>> JEFF: Got to have 12 disks.
Make sure you do.
>> Put them all in the boat.
Come on, Frosti!
>> Come on!
>> JEFF: Boat going in the
water.
Aaron and Erik heading back.
>> Come on, let's go, let's go,
let's go!
Come on.
Swim it in!
Come on, guys.
>> JEFF: Fei Long has all 12.
Jean-Robert pulls the boat in
the water, nearly loses the
disks.
>> Nothing spilled out, right?
>> No.
>> JEFF: It's a race back to
shore.
>> Come on, y'all
>> Aaron with the rope in his
teeth, man.
>> JEFF: Zhan Hu back first.
Got to get it up on that mat.
You're good!
Take over!
Get those disks up on to your
mat before you can start on the
puzzle.
Zhan Hu starts to work on the
Jean-Robert completely
exhausted.
>> Go, go, go!
>> JEFF: Got to get all 12
pieces before you can reveal the
puzzle board.
It is now a race between Todd,
Sherea and Denise, James, Peih-
Gee and Jaime.
>> Got one.
>> Got one, guys.
>> They fit.
>> JEFF: Fei Long making up a
lot of time.
They're now in the lead.
Jaime appears not to be
concerned at all.
You'd never know there was
anything on the line.
Denise, Sherea, Todd working as
hard as they can.
>> Here we go.
>> JEFF: They've locked in five
pieces.
Zhan Hu still with one.
>> They have to fit on, y'all.
They have to fit on like this.
>> The red.
>> JEFF: Fei Long working very
well together.
Nobody on this tribe wants to go
home.
Peih-Gee, you good at puzzles?
>> I'm good at sudoko.
>> ( bleep ) sudoko.
Pay attention.
>> JEFF: Fei Long getting very
close to winning this challenge.
Only two pieces left.
>> Switch, switch, switch.
>> Get it on!
Get it on!
>> JEFF: Fei Long wins immunity!
>> Good job, guys.
Good job.
>> JEFF: Zhan Hu, your extra
piece that really didn't come
into play anyway.
>> JEFF: Fei Long,
congratulations once again.
Immunity going home with you.
>> Thanks.
>> JEFF: Zhan Hu, definitely the
worst performance at a challenge
yet.
Had a big lead from Aaron and
Erik, and Jaime, Peih-Gee, and
James completely blew it.
Tribal council tonight.
Somebody going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head on back to camp.
>> Ah!
>> You can't handle pressure.
Like, I hollered at you.
And the puzzle girl, the one we
relied on, the brains of the
thing, she completely cracks and
starts talking about soduko.
And that's funny.
And then everything is funny.
>> It's not, like, a logical
kind of puzzle.
I mean, that's why.
I thought it, like, was a
logical... you just had to sit
and, like, try them all out.
>> Talking about soduko!
>> Jeff asked me a question.
What was I going to do, ignore
him?
>> Yes!
Yes!
Was Jeff's question that
important, or winning the
challenge?
Now somebody's ass got to go
home.
If you don't focus, I don't want
to hear it.
Especially during the game.
You're still not focusing?
Oh, goodness, gracious!
Y'all two guys need to figure
out which one of these girls is
going home, because we need a
strong team.
Y'all can play high school if
y'all want.
That's all I'm going to say.
I'm not babysitting a bunch of
children who just don't want to
do nothing and be funny during a
challenge.
Them girls are about to go
thirsty, because I just can't
support people who ain't going
to try.
So they might as well send me
home, you know, or cut one of
those girls.
>> What's up, dude?
>> Were they doing that in the
other challenges?
I mean, like, she's supposed to
be good at puzzles, and...
>> Oh, she completely dropped
the ball.
>> They always put her in there.
>> I think I just want go and
freakin' just try and get it out
of them.
>> Go talk to them.
>> They're right there.
>> Hi.
>> What the hell was that?
>> Are they kicking one of us
out, you think?
>> We threw the challenge.
>> I mean, I wouldn't have done
it...
>> I mean, I was laughing during
the whole thing.
I threw one of our pieces to the
other side.
>> Wait a minute, what?
>> Could you not tell we were
throwing it?
>> The two girls, they basically
threw it, you know, on purpose.
I didn't know that the girls
were going to throw it.
That puts me in a really tough
position.
I'm forced to... in this
situation, to stick with them.
Unfortunately, I'm really having
to trust them a lot, so I'm a
little worried about that.
I mean, I trust you still, and I
really, really want to keep
trusting you, you know?
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> Because I honestly want you
and I to stick together...
>> I think we should.
>> ...all the way to the finish,
really.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I just don't like losing,
especially on purpose, but I
want to remain in alliance with
Jaime, just because it's safe
for now at least.
Do we definitely vote off James
tonight?
>> Well, that's the thing.
>> Would you rather...
>> James is the one that was...
>> Pissed.
>> Talking.
I don't know why.
>> Okay.
>> Aaron and James definitely
are on the chopping block.
One of them's going home.
I just can't believe they didn't
figure it out.
I mean...
I trust James more than I do
Aaron for the simple fact that I
think Aaron's made enough
alliances on the other side
where he thinks he's set over
there.
And I think James probably
didn't have quite as many ties
at Fei Long.
So Aaron will be the first to
get kicked off.
>> I don't know.
I'm still shocked we lost so
bad.
>> Aaron really deserves to
stay.
>> Yeah, send my ass home.
>> Well, originally we had
agreed the first one to go was
going to be Aaron from the get-
go.
And we thought that we might be
able to get James onto our side.
I think after what happened
today, he doesn't trust us at
all, which means that tonight at
tribal council, we probably will
have to get rid of James.
>> Who are you guys voting?
>> The girls said James, man.
So I feel like I have to go with
what they say.
>> Right.
I don't trust, really, anyone
here on Zhan Hu.
You know, I'm on the chopping
block, and James is on the
chopping block.
But I think James is going to go
home.
So at tonight's tribal council,
I am going to vote for James.
Just so I won't have to vote for
Peih-Gee or I won't have to vote
for Jaime or anything like that,
so there's no hard feelings or
any kind of vendettas, you know.
So we'll see what happens.
>> JEFF: So let's talk about the
switch.
Jaime, what rationale went into
picking James and Aaron?
>> We wanted to break the other
team, and by taking their two
strongest they would be pretty
bad off.
>> JEFF: Aaron, was this good
news for you, or was this, "Oh,
man, everything's going so good
at Fei Long"?
>> Everything was going great at
Fei Long.
We were a really strong tribe.
We had posted a winning record.
And coming over here, we're the
new people, where it's three
against two.
And to lose immunity was a big
deal for us.
>> JEFF: I've got to say, we're
at tribal council, the place
where most anybody in this game
never wants to go, and Jaime's
smiling, got a little...
>> Yeah.
>> I'm not happy that I'm here,
but I'm not trying to be all
pissed off about it, either.
>> She has the numbers and she's
chillin'.
>> JEFF: What happened at the
challenge, Jaime?
I've been around a little bit in
this game.
It appeared to me as though you
had no concern about winning.
>> You know, if we merge we're
gone.
They've got the numbers.
As far as I'm concerned, I don't
want to be stuck with someone
that was going to go right back
to the other side.
>> JEFF: So I'm judging by the
lack of performance at today's
challenge you've decided you
can't trust Aaron and James, and
you threw the challenge.
>> Yes, sir.
>> JEFF: So Peih-Gee, the big
assumption you're making is
what?
>> Frosti and Sherea get voted
off, and then suddenly we merge,
guess what?
Now there's only three original
Zhan Hu members, seven Fei Long.
Hmm, I wonder who the next three
to get picked off are going to
be?
>> JEFF: James, this must drive
you nuts to watch people come
into a game that's really about
winning, and see them
continually lose, and then today
willingly lose.
>> And they're happy.
They're smiling.
I could never do that.
>> It's about winning the war.
It's not about winning the
battles.
>> You're not winning nothing.
You ain't...
>> James...
>> Then they asked me if I could
stay.
That's the funny... ask them.
Ask them.
>> I asked which one of you guys
wanted to stay the most.
>> What kind of sense does that
make?
What kind of dumb do you take me
for?
That's why they lose.
I told you all how I was going
to work.
I can't work with losers.
I can't do it.
>> JEFF: So James, does that
mean it's you tonight?
>> It should be.
They know how I am about this
losing thing.
They know how I am about not
going 100%.
I can't just sit here and just
watch these people dictate what
I'm going to do.
But I really don't want to go.
I love being here.
I love being here and
interacting and all this stuff,
but I just can't take another
loss like that.
>> JEFF: Aaron, what about you?
Do you plead your case and say,
"Well, I'd like to stay two more
days, three more days, whatever
you'll have me"?
>> You know what?
I want to be here as long as
possible.
I want to compete in every
challenge.
I want to be part of a team.
I want to last as long as I can.
>> JEFF: So you feel comfortable
that you're okay tonight.
>> I feel comfortable that I'm
okay tonight, but I brought my
bag anyway.
>> JEFF: Well, it's been pretty
clearly established that it's
going to be Aaron or James
tonight.
So let's end the mystery and see
who gets the guillotine.
It is time to vote.
Erik, you're up.
>> I wish I was sending all
three of those home.
It's good to do battle with you.
>> This is because I'm sticking
with my original teammates.
That's all I'm going with.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Peih-Gee.
James.
One vote Peih-Gee, one vote
Aaron.
James, one vote Aaron.
Two votes Aaron.
One vote Peih-Gee, one vote
James.
Fifth person voted out
of Survivor: China, Aaron.
That's three, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Take care, guys.
>> JEFF: Aaron, the tribe has
spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, Jaime, Peih-Gee, Erik, you
three are making a very
strategic play.
If your assumptions about the
game hold true, it could be a
good play.
If your assumptions are wrong,
could be trouble.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time
on Survivor...
>> Good hustle, baby.
>> JEFF: ...the search for the
hidden immunity idol gets warmer
and warmer.
First two, come up.
And the survivors get a
firsthand taste of local Chinese
cuisine.
>> I had no idea that I would be
going home tonight.
I thought it was going to be
James over me, and I just wanted
to say to James, I had a great
time slipping into battle with
you.
And I don't know what's going to
happen to you, buddy, but I'd
rather still be there on that
island with those people even
though I don't like them anymore
than be here talking about it.