>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Courtney grew closer to
Frosti...
>> Frosti's my little munchkin,
and he's a doll face.
>> PROBST: ...which made Todd
question her loyalty to the Fei
Long alliance.
>> It's scary.
It really is, because you never
know if she's going to want to
twist or turn.
>> PROBST: At the reward
challenge...
You will be divided into two
teams of four.
...Peih-Gee's team
dropped the ball.
James too hard, Peih-Gee can't
get it.
And Erik's team won an
unforgettable trip.
Frosti, Amanda, Erik and
Courtney, cruising down the Lee
River.
>> All right, everyone, cheers
to us.
>> PROBST: During the cruise,
Courtney and Amanda vented about
Peih-Gee.
>> She's too intense right now,
and I don't like that.
>> She's made a series of poor
decisions.
>> PROBST: And back at camp,
Peih-Gee blamed James for losing
the challenge...
...making her first in line to
be voted out.
>> Peih-Gee, she's just stupid.
>> PROBST: But at the immunity
challenge...
Peih-Gee wins immunity.
...Peih-Gee narrowly beat
Frosti.
With Peih-Gee immune, the former
Fei Long saw Frosti as the
biggest threat.
>> He has to go.
>> PROBST: And although James
had the only two hidden immunity
idols, he felt confident that he
wouldn't have to use them.
>> It makes no sense for us to
mess it up now, because it's
right there.
>> PROBST: And at tribal
council, his gamble paid off--
James received no votes.
Ninth person voted out and the
third member of our jury,
Frosti.
And Courtney lost a friend.
Frosti, the tribe has spoken.
All right.
Tonight, you will not be heading
directly back to camp.
We have more business to attend
to here.
Jury, it doesn't involve you.
You can head out.
Okay, we've just finished tribal
council.
Frosti was just voted out,
became the third member of our
jury.
There are now only seven of you
left.
Tonight, you're not going
directly back to camp...
because you're going to
participate in a reward
challenge right here at tribal
council.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Thank you!
>> PROBST: But this is no
ordinary reward.
The winner of the challenge will
travel by private jet hundreds
of miles into the Sungshan
mountains to a place where few
outsiders have ever been invited
to stay, the Shaolin Temple.
This is an incredible rare
privilege.
Built in the Fifth Century, the
Shaolin Temple is most famous
for being home to kung fu.
You'll enjoy a kung fu
demonstration, a vegetarian
meal.
You will then spend the night in
the temple before returning to
camp in the morning.
Big relief, James?
>> A little one.
>> PROBST: In the midst of a
crazy game, this truly is an
opportunity that very few people
in the world will ever
experience.
The winner of this challenge
will also choose two people to
go with them.
Let's get to it.
This reward challenge starts
right now.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> PROBST: For the Shaolin
Temple reward, I'm going to ask
you a series of questions based
on Chinese culture.
Each time you get one right, you
score a point.
First person to five wins
reward.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes, please.
>> PROBST: All right, beneath
your stools, black pouch.
Pull it out, remove your answer
cards, we'll get started.
Okay, first question.
True or false-- China is
credited with the invention of
the abacus.
Reveal.
Correct answer is true.
Todd got it right.
James got it right.
Peih-Gee got it right.
Denise got it right.
Next question.
Which animal does not belong to
the Chinese zodiac?
A, rat, B, rabbit, C, cat, or D,
rooster.
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer is C, cat.
Everybody got it right.
Nice job.
Next question.
True or false-- 99% of the giant
panda's diet is bamboo.
Everybody reveal.
Everybody except Denise said
true.
Still think you're right,
Denise?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Well, you're right
about that-- you're wrong.
The correct answer is true.
Everybody got it right except
Denise.
Here's where we're at--
Peih-Gee, James, and Todd have
three.
Everybody else has two.
Playing to five.
Next question.
The capital of China is:
A, Hong Kong, B, Beijing, C,
Shanghai, or D, Macao.
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer is Beijing, that
was B.
Everybody got it right except
Amanda.
Peih-Gee, James, Todd, you each
have four.
Everybody else has three.
Peih-Gee, James, or Todd could
win it on this question.
Here we go.
In Chinese culture, receiving a
red envelope means that inside
is A, a love letter, B, cash, C,
a death notice, or D, a military
draft notice.
Make a choice.
Everybody reveal.
Reveal, James.
Everybody's all over the board
with this one.
The correct answer is B, cash.
Peih-Gee wins reward.
>> Congratulations.
>> PROBST: All right, Peih-Gee,
take a spot over on the jury
bench.
>> Bye, baby.
>> PROBST: All right, Peih-Gee,
so you're going to the Shaolin
Temple, a rare experience.
Choose two people to come with
you.
>> I can't even look at you
guys.
I've got to pick Erik.
I'm sorry, but, like, we've been
so starving since, like, the
beginning of the season.
>> PROBST: Erik, take a spot
next to Peih-Gee.
>> Thank you, Peih-Gee.
>> PROBST: All right, Peih-Gee,
select one more person to join
you.
>> I'll take Denise.
>> PROBST: Denise, join Peih-Gee
and Erik.
Okay.
So everybody's going to go back
to camp together.
Try and get a little sleep,
because you're leaving very
early in the morning, Peih-Gee,
Erik, and Denise.
Have a good time.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night, guys.
>> Hey, guys, the boat.
>> Go eat a lot of food.
>> You guys don't have too much
fun here without us.
>> We'll do our best.
>> Peih-Gee picked me to see the
Shaolin Temple.
I got such love right now for
her.
But here I am, I'm going off
with Peih-Gee and Erik.
I'm concerned because sometimes
when you leave camp you don't
know what's going on, and when
you come back, you don't know
what to expect.
That makes me very, very
nervous.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Have fun.
Run, Erik, run!
>> Bye, guys.
>> Hey, I think we should eat a
lot today.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> It will be nice to have the
four of us chilling in a big
bed, eating good food.
This is what I want.
This is what, like, a nine-day
advance sneak preview?
We all know that, which I think
we're okay with.
When Denise, Peih-Gee, and Erik
left for their reward, we were
all kind of like, "Oh, this is
nice to have the four of us.
It could be this way.
We could keep it this way."
And there was no arguing.
>> Right now, the four of us are
in the proverbial Garden of
Eden.
The Lord said, "Don't bite that
apple."
If Eve would have listened, they
would be frolicking naked in
heaven.
I just want us to frolic naked
as long as we can.
So don't be tempted by Peih-Gee
and Erik.
Don't bite the apple.
Leave it alone.
>> We're in the top seven, soon
to be top four.
>> Yeah.
>> Right now, I'm just kind of
going along with everyone,
saying "Yeah, we're top four.
Whoo-hoo!"
But in all reality, I don't feel
comfortable going to the final
three with any of them.
This is the time in the game
that a change needs to be made.
This is my chance to make
something else happen the way I
want it to happen.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> Yeah!
>> You ever been on a private
jet?
>> I've never been on, like, a
charter jet before.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> It was a ridiculous contrast,
because we're still, like, in
crazy rags and we stink.
>> Here we are sitting in the
lap of luxury like millionaires
eating.
>> You and I didn't have to win.
>> Exactly.
>> Peih-Gee graced us.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> Thank you for having us.
>> You're welcome.
>> Here's to us flying high in
the skies.
>> Living large.
>> You guys realize that after
last night, we could be final
three?
Right now, the three of us,
that's three votes.
There's only seven people left.
We could get James to go with
us.
That's four of us.
That would be the majority.
We could pick off... who would
it be, Todd?
What do you think about that?
>> You never know what's going
to happen, though.
That's what this game is all
about.
>> Peih-Gee is working her
strategy.
She needs to do whatever she can
to get further along in this
game.
Peih-Gee and Erik are definitely
on the outsides, but you don't
want to make enemies, so, I
mean, we're just going to have
to wait and see what happens at
this point.
>> Welcome to Shaolin Temple.
>> Being Chinese, it was really
great to be able to experience
something that up until now had
kind of been, like, a separate
foreign world to me.
I mean, a 1,500-year-old Shaolin
temple, and it's huge.
You could see monks playing
music, some meditating.
You know, these are, like,
Shaolin monks and they're
renowned for their martial arts
prowess.
>> Yeah, I've been actually
taking karate classes and I
opened my own school.
My black belt is coming up.
>> Cool.
>> Eight years.
So just... I started when I was
32, and I'm 40 now.
So still a student.
Some might say.
Not me yet.
Out of all the rewards that have
come up, this is the one I
wanted to go on the most.
The Shaolin Temple.
It's 1,500 years old.
I mean, just to look around and
see over 1,000 years of culture
and the beginnings of the actual
martial arts themselves is just
so incredible for me.
It's just an amazing thing.
The demonstration was fantastic.
I mean, it takes years of
practice just to get a single
form down, and these guys were
doing it with hardly any effort.
>> After the main kung fu
exhibition, the cutest kids came
out.
Denise and Peih-Gee and I were
allowed to go down, and they
were teaching us some moves.
>> Going to burn off those
cookies.
>> Are you getting this, Denise?
You're getting it for sure.
>> A little demonstration.
>> Sure, put me on the spot.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> It was cool to see Denise do
that karate.
I was impressed.
I was, like, "No way.
Denise, who knew?"
>> At this point, I could not
thank Peih-Gee enough for
picking me for this reward.
To take that experience back
home for the rest of my life,
there's no words to really
describe that.
>> Wow!
Do we just dig in?
>> I guess so.
>> We've forgotten what to do
with food.
>> Oh, that's good.
>> That's sweet and sour, huh?
>> Mmm!
Oh, my god.
It's so good.
We've been squatting on logs
eating out of, like, dirty
utensils.
So, like, suddenly we're ushered
into this, like, magical setting
in the middle of the temple
courtyard.
I mean, it was... it was really,
really cool.
What did you think of that
demonstration, huh?
In those guys are crazy out
there.
>> That was cool, huh?
>> It was so awesome.
>> I've never seen anything like
that.
>> It's an amazing reward.
Oh, my god, this is our room,
you guys.
>> Beautiful.
>> This is really cool.
>> Good night.
Thank you for such a good day.
>> We got to sleep in, like, a
little temple room, and they set
up mats.
And, I mean, it was just... it
was crazy.
Like, you couldn't... I don't
think you could, like, pay to do
something like that.
My neck is still on the line.
People still want me out.
But being at the temple, it
really gives me inspiration, you
know, for me to really to keep
on truckin'.
>> Yeah.
>> This rainstorm is hell.
When you're sitting in a muddy
hole in a swimming suit that
you've been wearing for a month,
crammed, hunched over like this,
looking out, praying for the
clouds to go away... I'm done
with the rain, done.
Oh, my gosh.
>> They're back.
>> When we came back to camp
this afternoon, there was nobody
around, and I didn't understand
where everybody was.
Amanda came out to greet
everybody.
Nobody's going to come out to
greet Peih-Gee and Erik.
>> Hey.
How was your kung fu?
>> It was pretty sweet.
>> It was?
>> Yeah, it was really cool.
>> That's cool.
>> Where is everybody, in the
cave?
>> Yeah.
>> Hey, guys.
I won't lie.
It was, like, pretty cool.
The three of us, we had this
great experience.
We get back here, and it is,
like, a mess.
And, obviously, they're like
miserable rats here.
>> So what did you guys do?
>> You flew somewhere?
>> Yeah.
>> It was pretty cool.
It was, like, a little small jet
and we had pistachios and a
bottle of champagne.
We get there and we walked
around and they showed us a bit
of the stuff.
>> You're lying.
Chocolate?
>> No, they were, like, pecan
sandies.
>> I was about to push you back
in the mud.
>> The cave was the best thing I
have right now.
The cave is my happy place.
What I don't want, like, is
everyone and their damn mother
decides that they like the cave,
too.
It's like, you know, Peih-Gee
comes sidling up in there.
And I'm like, "I'm going to kill
you."
And then you want to start
talking about... no, get out of
here.
Get out.
No talking in the cave.
>> We're all really happy that
you guys got to go, especially
you...
>> Man.
Man.
Peih-Gee is not my idea of fun.
She is annoying as hell.
She goes to Denise and is like,
"We should vote out Todd, dah,
dah, dah."
And I'm thinking, "Bitch, do you
expect anybody to get up on your
side?
Anybody?"
Good job, because now I hate
your guts.
Thank you.
>> Oh, no!
>> That's true.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I get it.
Erik's not that smart.
If I were to go from nice happy
five to the evil two... I'm not
going to eat that apple.
They can tempt me all they want,
but I'm just not having it.
He should know that.
He should know that I'm really
not going to flip on nobody.
It's pointless.
>> I'm over the bamboo.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, gosh.
"Practice, practice, practice,
anyone can win this game.
Arrogance breeds complacency.
Remember that when you lose your
flame."
So we're just flinging stars at
people?
Like, isn't this kind of
dangerous?
>> When we go back... I have
been up all night, thinking of
our situation.
I have a really good idea.
We get rid of James tonight.
I do.
Because the thing is, to get
James out, he can't expect it,
and he doesn't expect it right
now.
I came up with a plan to get rid
of James, because he's in
control right now, because he
has the immunity idols.
So he definitely has to be
blindsided tonight.
We're pretty much, like, just
giving James a top three spot
right now.
And he deserves to win a million
dollars.
I would give James a million
He's done the most around camp.
He's been, like, crazy good in
challenges.
There's no other time to get rid
of James other than right now.
>> Okay, that sounds good.
>> Is that a good idea?
>> Yeah.
>> James keeps telling everyone,
"Stay away from the apple.
Don't eat the apple.
This is our final four, that's
it."
I am not only ready to bite the
apple, I am ready to make the
whole frickin' pie.
All we have to do is make sure
he doesn't win immunity today.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Final seven.
You ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Peih-Gee, time to give it up.
>> Oh, come back soon.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
each throw three stars at a
series of targets, each worth
different points.
Hit any part of the target, and
get one, two, or three points.
Hit the heart itself, you get
five points.
The three people with the
highest scores at the end of the
first round move on to a sudden
death round, where you only get
one throw.
The person with the highest
score wins immunity, is safe
tonight at tribal council,
guaranteed a one in-- what,
Todd?--
>> Six!
>> PROBST: ...shot at a million
dollars.
We'll draw for spots, we'll get
started.
Peih-Gee is up first.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Three stars.
Looking to score as many points
as you can.
First toss, in the ground.
>> I suck.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee hits the
board, no score.
One throw left.
You need to get some points
here.
Oh, hits the black but bounces
off.
Peih-Gee scores zero.
Next up, Todd.
The mark to beat is zero.
Todd with his first throw.
Oh, just misses.
Second shot.
Low.
One star left.
Todd scores three.
You move into the first spot.
Three is now the mark to beat.
>> Too high, too low, right in
there.
Ouch!
>> PROBST: Erik, you're up.
Southpaw scores with three his
first throw.
Just misses another three.
>> Oh!
>> So close.
>> PROBST: Another three.
Erik scores six points, moves
into first place.
Todd slides down in second
place...
>> Good job, Erik, that was
awesome.
>> PROBST: ...with three points.
Courtney, you're up.
>> Come on, Court.
>> Thanks, Amanda.
>> PROBST: One point gets you
into the top three, Courtney.
>> Well, we'll see how this
goes.
>> PROBST: Courtney nails a
three, moving you into second
place already.
>> Oh, a score!
>> Good job, babe.
>> PROBST: Courtney just misses
the three.
You hit the two.
That is five points total.
And Courtney with another one.
That's six.
Courtney moves into the top
position with Erik.
Courtney now has six, Erik has
six, Todd has three.
Peih-Gee you're out of the
running.
James, you're up.
Three is now the score to beat.
You've got to have three to get
into the top three.
James throws that flat.
James scores three.
James scores another three.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: James now has six.
>> Good job, James.
>> PROBST: James, move up here,
James, Courtney, Erik, each with
six.
Todd is now out of the running.
Amanda, you're up.
Nice soft toss gets Amanda
three.
Oh, hits the three but it
bounces off.
You need another three at least.
And she just gets it.
Amanda scores six.
It is now Amanda, James,
Courtney, and Erik, all tied at
six.
Anything less than six, you are
out of this challenge.
Denise, you know what you have
to do.
Oh, first throw bounces off.
>> Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Denise with a two.
Denise, one throw left.
You have only one thing you can
hit, and that is the heart for
five.
Oh, just misses.
Bounces off, not enough for
Denise.
We were looking for the top
three, but instead we have a top
four.
Amanda, James, Courtney, and
Erik, all tied at six.
All four will move on to the
final round.
I'll go set it up.
For the final round you each get
one throw apiece.
The target is ten feet further
back.
Courtney, you're up.
Courtney scores nothing.
Take a spot.
>> It's a little further this
time.
>> PROBST: Amanda, you're up.
You know what you need to do.
>> Yep.
Amanda sitting on two.
You're currently in first place.
>> Good job, babe.
>> PROBST: Erik, you're up.
Erik scores three, moves into
first place.
James.
Immunity and a guaranteed one in
six shot at winning this game if
you score more than three
points.
You have one star to throw.
James can't do it.
Erik wins individual immunity.
Erik, come on over.
>> Good job, Erik.
>> Good job, man.
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: You are safe tonight
at tribal council.
For the rest of you, after 30
days, this game will come to an
end for one of you.
See you guys at tribal.
Head on back.
>> Good job, Erik.
>> Yeah, good job.
>> Congratulations, man.
>> Thank you.
>> Well, the immunity challenge
was okay.
I mean, Erik got the immunity.
So we get rid of Peih-Gee
tonight, and then after that,
focus on getting rid of Erik,
and then it's all cake after
that.
>> Okay.
>> We're pretty much giving
James a top three position right
now, because you know everyone
is going to vote for him.
I guarantee you.
Why don't we take control and
vote him out tonight?
>> I just worry, honestly, more
about getting Erik and Peih-Gee
anywhere near, because they are
the fighters.
>> She hasn't won anything.
>> She won two in a row!
>> Yeah, but, see, the next
challenge, if Peih-Gee has
immunity, then Erik goes.
If not, then Peih-Gee goes.
You see what I'm saying?
>> Yeah.
>> What do you want to do?
>> I will do what everybody
feels most comfortable
doing.
I don't care what that is.
>> There is a chance that James
could use the hidden immunity
idol.
I mean, why not, you know?
If he pulls out the idol, all of
our votes for James go away, so
we just have to continue to
convince him that we're voting
Peih-Gee out-- basically, lie to
his face, which hurts really
bad, especially since I like the
guy.
But I like a million dollars,
too.
>> I hope we can keep
redeeming ourself.
Erik, look at this.
There's one last card I could
play, which is that I'm pretty
sure that James has the immunity
idol.
So I'm going to try.
I'm still going to talk to
them and see.
I don't want to go out without a
fight, you know?
>> Yes.
I'm not stupid, Peih-Gee.
>> No, no, no.
Peih-Gee...
>> I'm debating, as far as
whether I would go along with
Peih-Gee.
On one hand, if I voted for Todd
and then James gave the idol and
Todd was gone, that would be
kind of good, but then I'm
risking a lot by doing that.
>> That girl there, she's on her
hustle.
>> I know.
>> Which I don't blame her.
That's how she's supposed to be.
>> Exactly.
She knows she's leaving tonight.
She knows.
No, she knows.
>> Then we go with the good
stuff.
Why play around with it?
It's right there.
>> I know.
>> It's right there.
>> I've been the main guy trying
to hold this thing together, and
that's what I'm going to do.
Tonight is pivotal.
We get past tonight, I'm good.
If I get a sense that somebody
is going to do something they're
not supposed to do, I will play
the idol.
I'd have to.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of your jury.
Jaime, Jean-Robert, and Frosti,
voted out at the last tribal
council.
First thing I've got to ask--
Denise, you are beaming like I
have not seen you beam in 30
days.
Tell me about the reward.
>> It was so much fun, Jeff.
The energy just from being in
the temple, I mean, it just gave
me such a lift.
I mean, I got plenty of energy
now to go the rest of the time.
>> PROBST: Peih-Gee, have you
tried to penetrate this former
Fei Long group?
>> Yeah.
I mean, it's still like butting
against a brick wall because
they're just absolutely
convinced it's numbers, it's
numbers.
>> PROBST: James, for all the
talk of Fei Long sticking
together, Peih-Gee is still in
this game, just like you.
>> Yes, she is.
>> PROBST: So whatever she was
doing, it's working just like
your strategy.
>> It is working.
I mean, she's doing what she's
supposed to do.
She's working hard at it.
She's been working hard at it
all day.
But I'm like this-- it's so much
easier to fight from a definite
five than it is to guess and
take a chance.
But as far as right now, there's
still a Zhan Hu here, and you
get them off.
You know, why are we going to
allow them to keep on losing to
win, or just slide in?
>> That's not accurate because,
after all, who has been winning
individual immunity?
Oh, Erik, that's a lovely
necklace you've got on.
So calling us losers isn't going
to make us too happy.
You guys have to realize these
are going to be people that
eventually you're going to want
voting for you in the end,
right?
>> PROBST: Todd, scale of one to
ten, how important is trust?
>> Trust is huge.
I'd say probably a ten.
If you don't have that necklace
around your neck, you know, what
else can you do?
>> PROBST: Well, the opposite
would be not trust.
>> Yeah, I mean, it's kind of
like keep your friends close,
keep your enemies closer, you
know?
>> PROBST: Denise, what's your
take on trust?
>> I don't trust anybody at all.
You say, "Okay, I make a pact
with you," but then four other
people decide, "You know, that's
not a very good pact, so we're
going to take you out before we
take the other person out."
You know, you never know if it's
going to be you.
>> PROBST: James, is it possible
you could trust somebody at this
point?
>> It's possible in a way if you
have the same strategy, if you
have the same goal with them.
That's the only time you could
really trust somebody.
If you know that they really
need you and you really need
them, you all bond together.
But if not, you really can't
trust anybody.
>> PROBST: Who here will admit
that they're not overly
concerned that it could be them
tonight?
( laughter )
So after this entire tribal
council, five strong, two weak,
everybody here truly feels it
could be them.
Peih-Gee, what do you think your
odds are?
There's only two Zhan Hu left,
and Erik is wearing individual
immunity.
>> Hey, man, I've never harbored
any illusions to the contrary.
So I've never been in doubt
about my place in this group.
I've been expecting it to be me
every single night.
Tonight's no different.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Erik, you have immunity.
If you wanted to give it to
somebody you could.
No chance.
Erik is the only person you
cannot vote for.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
>> Just a little insurance, I
guess.
>> If he'd lost you'd still be
here.
Hope this works.
If not, I'm scared for my life.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
If anyone has a hidden immunity
idol, now would be the time to
play it.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Todd.
James.
One vote Todd, one vote James.
Peih-Gee.
One vote Todd, one vote James,
one vote Peih-Gee.
James.
Two votes James, one vote Todd,
one vote Peih-Gee.
James.
That's three votes James, one
vote Todd, one vote Peih-Gee.
Tenth person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury,
James.
That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
James, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> PROBST: Tonight's tribal
council said it all.
You have nine days left.
They're going to be interesting.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
The tribe is overwhelmed with
emotion.
Amanda turns on her closest
ally.
And everyone's fate is in the
hands of Denise.
>> I'm definitely the swing vote
tonight.
For me, personally, I mean, this
is do or die.
>> I have the two idols, I guess
I should have played them.
I'm kind of disappointed in
myself.
I kind of caught a feeling, but
I still didn't do it.
Dealing with those people and
trying to hold those Froot Loops
together this whole damn time,
it was killing me.
You can't be angry with anybody.
It's a game.
I mean, they played their best
hand.
They did what they were supposed
to do.
I rolled the dice too many times
and I just got caught off.