>> Ah!
>> JEFF PROBST: Previously
on Survivor...
The tribes were mixed up.
>> "Fei Long, choose the two
warriors from Zhan Hu who you
feel can best help to strengthen
your tribe."
>> JEFF: Sherea and Frosti had
to move to the Fei Long tribe.
>> Hey, guys!
>> Hello!
>> JEFF: Aaron and James had to
move to the Zhan Hu tribe.
>> What's going on, guys?
>> JEFF: At the new Fei Long,
Sharea and Frosti were
outnumbered.
>> This is a dangerous place for
me.
Things are really messed up now.
>> JEFF: But they quickly
noticed that Jean-Robert was on
the outs.
>> I know.
>> That just makes me so much
more comfortable knowing that
there's somebody here they
already have problems with.
>> JEFF: Meanwhile, Todd
continued the search for the
hidden immunity idol.
>> "Waste no more time searching
the ground."
>> Right now, I'm kind of
wandering around the camp, like,
with my head in the sky.
>> JEFF: At the new Zhan Hu,
Jaime and Peih-Gee hatched a
plan to lose immunity challenges
on purpose.
>> JEFF: And at the immunity
challenge, Jaime tossed away a
puzzle piece...
>> They have to fit on, y'all.
They have to fit on like this.
>> JEFF: ...barely disguising
her effort to throw the
challenge.
Fei Long wins immunity!
At tribal council, the plan was
uncovered.
So you threw the challenge.
>> Yes, sir.
>> JEFF: And Aaron was voted
out...
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: China, Aaron.
...leaving James on the Zhan Hu
chopping block.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
>> Good morning, James.
>> I definitely feel confident
about throwing the challenge and
getting Aaron off the game.
He was one of the most powerful
players, and suddenly we had
full control of him, and we
still have that over James.
If we throw the next immunity
challenge, James is going to be
gone.
Best possible scenario, we merge
at that point.
And if that happens, we'll be
able to reconnect with Frosti
and Sherea, still... if they're
still on the same page with us.
>> Aaron's gone.
And I'm just at their mercy
right now.
The best thing for me to do
is to keep them rested so in
competitions, there's no excuse
of anybody being tired.
It makes me look good in the
long run.
They're going to keep me around.
So I'm trying to deal with it
and make it work.
Because if they throw another
challenge, I'm gone.
( snoring )
>> I have to tell you something.
It has to stay between us.
There's a hidden immunity idol
here at our camp.
When we kidnap people, they give
us clues.
And I've gotten them all.
And I wasn't going to tell you
until I found it, but I haven't
found it yet.
I have three clues.
>> Todd approached me and he
told me that he had three clues
to the immunity idol, which I
was kind of shocked because I
didn't know about any hidden
immunity idol.
So we're going to do everything
we can to find that idol today.
We have to.
>> If we win reward today, we
are bringing over either Aaron
or James, whoever is left,
because they're going to give us
a clue as to where that hidden
immunity idol is, and Amanda and
I will have control in this
game.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
Fei Long getting your first look
at the new Zhan Hu.
Aaron voted out at the last
tribal council.
You guys ready to get to today's
reward challenge?
>> Yes, sir.
>> JEFF: For today's challenge,
one person from each tribe will
race through this abandoned
Chinese village to find a tribe-
colored puzzle board.
You'll untie it, bring it back
to your mat, the next person
goes.
Once you've collected all eight
boards, you'll use them to
decode a phrase made famous by
Confucius.
First tribe to solve it
correctly wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: The winning tribe will
be taken to a nearby island that
is home to a tea house.
You'll have access to a bath,
shower, chance to get clean,
plenty of soap, towels.
You will have two Western
toilets, something you haven't
had in a while.
Plenty of Charmin, ultra-strong.
And because it's a tea house,
you'll have some tea and a light
snack.
In addition, the winning tribe
will kidnap one person from the
losing tribe.
That person will stay with them
until the next immunity
challenge.
Big enough stakes?
>> Love it.
>> JEFF: Fei Long, you have
three extra members.
You're sitting three people out.
Keeping in mind you cannot sit
out the same people in back-to-
back challenges, who are the
three people sitting out?
Denise, Amanda, Courtney,
sitting this one out.
I'll give everybody else a
minute to strategize and we'll
get started.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready?
Go.
James and Jean-Robert moving
from room to room.
>> What in the world?
>> JEFF: Got to get the planks
untied and race back before the
next person can go.
>> Come on, Jean-Robert!
>> JEFF: Jean-Robert first back
with a plank for Fei Long.
Sherea heading out.
James back with a plank for Zhan
Hu.
Peih-Gee heading out.
>> Come on, Sherea!
>> That's mine.
>> Sorry.
>> Concentrate, Sherea.
>> Come on, Peih-Gee, you've got
it girl!
>> Pull that out, let's go!
Way to go, yeah!
>> JEFF: Sherea has her plank.
She's heading back.
Todd out for Fei Long.
>> Come on, Todd!
>> All right, Peih-Gee.
You got this.
>> Come on, Peih-Gee.
>> JEFF: Peih-Gee back with
another plank.
Erik out for Zhan Hu.
>> Come on, Todd!
>> Charmin time!
Western toilets, baby!
>> JEFF: Todd back with another
plank for Fei Long.
Frosti out for Fei Long.
Erik back for Zhan Hu with a
plank.
Frosti back with another plank
for Fei Long.
Jaime coming back with another
plank.
James now for Zhan Hu.
>> Focus, Sherea.
You got this!
>> JEFF: Sherea coming back with
another plank for Fei Long.
>> Go for it!
You got it!
>> JEFF: Fei Long has only three
planks left.
>> Good job, James.
>> JEFF: James back with another
plank for Zhan Hu.
Peih-Gee heading back out.
>> Yeah, baby!
Come on!
Put the heat on, baby!
Put the heat on!
>> JEFF: Jean-Robert letting
everybody know he's got a plank.
Todd heading out for Fei Long.
Fei Long with six planks now.
Peih-Gee back with another plank
for Zhan Hu.
Zhan Hu now with six planks.
>> Keep it up!
Todd, you got it!
>> JEFF: Todd back with another
plank for Fei Long.
Erik heading back with the
seventh plank for Zhan Hu.
James goes back out.
We are tied, seven planks each.
Each tribe has one plank left
before they can start working on
the puzzle.
Frosti back with the eighth and
final plank for Fei Long.
They start working on their
puzzle.
It is a phrase made famous by
Confucius.
>> Come on, James!
>> JEFF: Zhan Hu patiently
waiting on James to get back.
Here he comes.
Go, Zhan Hu!
Zhan Hu, trying to catch up.
>> Right there.
>> JEFF: Fei Long working on
their puzzle.
Nice reward on the line, and the
kidnapping of a tribe member
from the other tribe.
Frosti getting excited.
He thinks he's on to something.
Fei Long thinks they have
something.
Trying to figure out what it is.
>> Where's the O?
Where's the one with the O on
it?
>> JEFF: Zhan Hu making no
progress, once again having a
very difficult time with the
puzzle part of a challenge.
>> Tell me when.
I can't see.
>> Is that right?
>> We've got it.
>> JEFF: "The journey of a
thousand miles begins with a
single step."
Fei Long wins reward!
All right, first order of
business: Fei Long, you are
kidnapping one member from Zhan
Hu.
They will stay with you until
the next immunity challenge,
which means they will
participate in this reward with
you.
Who you getting?
>> Bring him back, baby.
>> Come back, James.
Come on home.
Come home for a night, son.
Haven't seen you smile like that
in a minute.
>> JEFF: Zhan Hu, got nothing
for you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
James, this is for you.
It says "open in private."
That's what it means.
Even though are you friendly
with these guys.
Fei Long, congratulations.
This is yours, and you are
heading to your reward.
A boat is waiting for you.
Get your stuff, head on out.
>> When Jeff announced what the
reward was at the challenge,
there was excitement on the
team.
We're going to go to a tea house
and some refreshment.
That's what he said, "Tea house,
some refreshment and showers."
But when we got to this place,
it was like a little sweet spot
in the middle of nowhere.
The view was amazing.
I mean, everybody on the tribe
was just so happy.
>> Hello.
>> Welcome to the Charmin Tea
House.
>> Come in and have some tea.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Wow!
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> No!
>> Oh, my god!
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, my gosh, sugar!
>> They sit us down and they
give us tea, and then they bring
out little snacks, and we're all
so happy to be there.
Oh!
It was so good!
>> Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah!
>> Okay.
>> Yeah!
What a great challenge to win.
This is ridiculous.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Oh, my god, you have a brush!
>> This is so nice!
>> Isn't it, though?
>> For real.
This is the best reward.
>> I'd like my watermelon in the
tub, please.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, this is the best day
ever.
>> I won't lie to you, Frosti
and James.
That tub looks the most
attractive to jump into right
now.
That tub right there.
>> I am so happy right now.
>> I tried my best to be as far
away from Jean-Robert in the
bathtub as could possibly happen
in that place.
He had the one on the far end,
I took the one on the other far
end.
He's kind of gross.
Every single part of me wants to
see Jean-Robert go.
I just don't like him.
He's a horrible person.
>> Oh, there we go!
We've got some butt action
happening!
>> Whoo!
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah, James!
>> Don't tease me, James!
Don't tease me!
>> James has such a nice butt.
He was in the shower, lathering
up.
He's stripping down, and none of
us cared.
He has a nice butt.
I mean, he might as well show it
off.
>> Why y'all messing with me?
>> I'll speak for myself.
I'm tired of losing.
>> We're so into keeping Sherea
Frosti, Erik, Peih-Gee and I
together.
We thought we would do anything
to save them-- we'd throw a
challenge to save them.
We did it, you know?
But Frosti won't make eye
contact with us.
We don't know if he's changed
his mind and switched over with
them.
You know, everything's just
unknown, so it's really hard to
deal with, especially when
there's just three of us here
and there's so many over there.
>> Now I'm not sure about Frosti
and Sherea, because that flips
everything.
>> I mean, we have three right
here, three strong.
That's great.
>> But it's not enough.
>> This the best reward yet.
>> It's so nice to clean my
feet.
This is the life.
>> You know, sometimes
throughout this game, I feel
like I am the only one playing.
So I knew right away when we
kidnapped James that I would
approach him.
>> "In this sealed tube is a
clue to the hidden immunity
idol.
You must give this to a member
of this tribe before you rejoin
your own."
Cool.
I hope it's worth it.
I need something to save me.
I'm in a bad spot right now.
Todd is the cornerstone to all
the alliances on this tribe, so
I'm going to roll with Todd and
roll the old dice and maybe it
will come up right.
If not, I'm pretty much gone
anyway, so I have to do it.
>> "There are four that surround
it, and four much the same.
The one etched finer could
salvage the game."
I know what they're talking
about.
It's those stupid bats above the
freakin' thing.
>> I went over where we thought
the idol would be, and I was
just hitting off shingles so
people didn't know what I was
doing.
And then Todd comes over...
>> Knock those down.
>> He gets up there, and he
starts pulling on the thing.
>> All of a sudden, Frosti comes
running over and climbs up, so I
go into panic mode of, "He's
going to find out.
He's going to see this!"
And Amanda's like, "Get down,
Frosti, get down, Frosti,"
because she knows about it.
And I'm telling him to get down,
and I started panicking, and...
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait, wait, wait!
>> What?
>> All I could think was Frosti,
Frosti, no!
>> This has to be the worst way
in history of getting an
immunity idol.
Like, honestly, in front of
everybody, Todd's yelling.
He's so impatient.
I knew something like that was
going to happen.
>> Being there when they got the
idol cements my place in their
little group.
I'm there for sure.
Frosti's in.
In!
>> James came down.
I gave him the idol, and I told
him what needs to happen.
This is it.
>> Yeah.
>> You've just got to lose the
game.
>> So if James takes that idol,
loses immunity, they vote for
him, but he uses the idol to get
rid of Jaime, we sever the tie
between her and Erik.
Hopefully, at ten we'll merge,
and we'll still have our numbers
to go strong into the merge.
Now, here's the way it works.
Everybody votes.
You stand up and say, "Jeff, I
have the hidden immunity idol."
All of your votes are immune.
The person you vote for is gone.
>> Cool.
>> You can make that Jaime.
>> I cannot stop smiling.
And it's all good, because I'm
not going anywhere.
I have the immunity idol.
It's all good, baby.
>> I don't know if the clues are
the same as theirs, but they
might be.
The second you get to camp,
their camp, you run up and you
grab it off.
>> Cool.
I was going to do that anyway.
>> But do it without them
noticing.
>> I'm the only one with real
access to the other immunity
idol at the other tribe.
So now all I have to do is stay
focused, keep my head in the
game, lose the immunity
challenge, get the other idol.
Now I have both of them.
I mean, it's going to be
wonderful.
I'm having a great time.
>> This saved our asses.
>> Jaime, all right.
>> Do you know how?
I found the hidden immunity
idol.
>> You found it?
>> I gave it to James for them
to lose and get rid of Jaime.
So we still have our numbers.
>> How did you find it?
>> See that empty square up
there?
>> No way, just right there in
front of everybody.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> James knows to throw the
challenge.
>> I can't believe it.
Here it was sitting right in
front of us at camp the whole
darn time.
>> So I will be doing my best,
as I always give 110%, because
that's the only way I know how
to go.
>> Me telling Courtney and
Denise about the hidden immunity
idol helped them realize that
they had to try harder for
immunity today, especially if
they're fighting to lose, which
we don't even know is the case.
>> Over at Zhan Hu, I'm pretty
much a dead man walking.
But now I have the upper hand.
They think they're safe-- wrong.
I'll be able to get them.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
So James, time to head back to
your tribe, Zhan Hu.
>> JEFF: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's immunity
challenge?
First things first, Todd.
Take back immunity.
Once again, immunity back up for
grabs.
Today's challenge will be a
food-eating competition.
You're going to eat traditional
Chinese dishes that are anything
but pleasant.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Oh, gross.
>> One at a time, players from
each tribe will step up and
square off.
The first person to get their
food down scores a point for
their tribe.
The first tribe to four wins
immunity, safe in this game.
Make sense?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> JEFF: Fei Long, you have
three extra members.
You're sitting three people out.
You cannot sit the same people
out in back-to-back challenges.
Courtney, Amanda, and Denise sat
out in the last challenge.
You are playing in this
challenge.
You need one more member to join
them.
>> That's going to be Frosti.
>> JEFF: Frosti.
Everybody else take a spot on
the bench.
We'll get started.
First two come up.
Frosti taking on Peih-Gee.
>> Come on, Frosti.
You own this.
>> JEFF: Chinese name for
this, ghi ching.
You know what that is?
>> No.
>> JEFF: Chicken hearts.
>> Oh, yeah.
You own this!
>> Oh, my god.
>> JEFF: Ten each.
Got to get all ten down.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Peih-Gee shoving them down.
Frosti shoving them down.
>> Swallow them, Peih-Gee.
>> Oh, Frosti, don't enjoy them,
swallow them.
>> Swallow, Peih-Gee, swallow.
>> That's it, Frosti, good job.
>> JEFF: Frosti making quick
work of the chicken hearts.
He's got to get them down now.
>> Oh, that's beautiful.
>> JEFF: He's licking the plate.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> What?
>> JEFF: For emphasis.
Fei Long scores.
Fei Long leads, one-zip.
Next two, Jaime and Courtney.
Nizho is the Chinese name for
this.
You guys got off easy-- eel.
>> Oh, cool.
>> JEFF: Three pieces of eel
Got to get all of it down,
including the heads.
Fei Long leads one-zip for
immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Come on, Jaime.
>> Good job, Courtney.
>> JEFF: Courtney and Jaime both
attacking the eel.
Probably the best food you've
had in 18 days.
Jaime not messing around.
She's already on her second
piece of eel.
Courtney still working on the
first.
Jaime working on her third piece
of eel.
>> Come on, Courtney.
>> JEFF: Jaime finishing up her
third piece of eel.
Courtney catching up.
Courtney now done with her
second piece of eel.
>> There's the puking, there's
the gagging.
There it comes.
Here it comes.
>> Go, Courtney.
Swallow it, swallow it,
Courtney.
Keep going.
>> JEFF: Jamie on her last bit.
Courtney trying to shove the
last of her eel down.
Jaime has it.
Zhan Hu scores.
We're tied one-one.
Next two, come up.
>> Do this, Amanda.
>> All right, Erik, you're
hungry.
>> JEFF: Jhing zeng wei is the
name of this dish.
Baby turtles.
>> Oh, my god.
We have to eat the shell and
everything?
>> JEFF: Three each.
We're tied one-one for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Amanda throws the first two in
her mouth.
Erik working one at a time.
>> Wow, Amanda!
You're a champion, Amanda!
>> Swallow, swallow, swallow,
swallow, swallow.
>> JEFF: Erik and Amanda both
have all three in their mouths.
Just got to get them down.
Show me an empty mouth.
>> Swallow, Amanda!
Swallow, swallow, swallow,
Amanda.
Swallow, Amanda!
Swallow it!
>> JEFF: Erik has it.
Zhan Hu leads two-one.
Playing to four.
Next two.
Denise and James.
Chinese name for this, mau dje
don.
Balut is the name we call it.
These are chicken fetuses.
>> Come on, Denise.
You can do this.
>> JEFF: You each have two.
They've been weighed.
It is equal portions.
They still have the feathers on
them, so be careful of that when
they go down.
Zhan Hu leads two-one.
Playing to four.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Ah!
>> JEFF: James spitting it back
up.
>> Come on, James.
It's a cheeseburger.
Oh, it's a sandwich.
>> Get in my mouth!
Ah!
Get in there.
Aaggh!
>> JEFF: Denise takes a big
chunk of feathers.
James struggling.
>> James, you're going to let
Denise show you up?
>> JEFF: James spitting it back
up into his bowl.
>> Over in two seconds.
>> Just swallow it, Denise.
You got this, own it!
>> JEFF: Denise, you're
struggling.
Mind over matter.
>> That's the way, Denise.
Denise puts it down, and it
comes right back up.
>> Oh, Denise, you've got him.
>> Denise, you've got him.
He's gagging on it, Denise.
>> Oh, yeah, he's full from
breakfast.
>> Are you giving up, James?
Give me a break.
You going to let Denise beat
you.?
>> You've got this James.
>> Put it in your mouth, hold
your nose, chew and swallow.
>> Yeah, hold your nose, James.
>> Sorry, James.
>> JEFF: Denise, you giving up?
>> No way Denise is giving up.
>> Denise, come on.
>> I got it.
>> Oh, god.
>> Chew it.
>> JEFF: James puts it all in
his mouth.
>> Come on, man.
>> JEFF: James scores for Zhan
Hu.
Zhan Hu leads 3-1.
>> You are the man!
Give him some water.
Good job, Denise.
>> JEFF: Next two, come up.
Frosti coming up for Fei Long.
Erik coming back for Zhan Hu.
Everybody's gone once.
We're on the second round.
Pei dhong is the name.
Thousand-year-old egg.
Put a little clay around them,
some ash to keep them preserved.
I promise you this will not be
the best thing you've ever
eaten, and it will rival
anything you've tried before.
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: Here's where we stand.
Zhan Hu leads three-one.
Frosti, if you do not win this
point, Zhan Hu wins immunity.
Eric, win this point, you win
immunity for Zhan Hu.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Frosti is not messing around at
all.
Get it all in there.
>> Come on, Frost.
Erik's got it for Zhan Hu.
Zhan Hu wins immunity.
>> Good job, Frost.
Zhan Hu, congratulations.
No tribal council tonight,
nobody going home.
>> Yes!
>> Finally.
>> JEFF: Fei Long, tribal
council tonight where one of the
seven of you will be going home.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
I'll see you at tribal.
>> See you, guys.
>> Heads up high, guys, because
we played well.
Denise, you got brutalized.
That was, like... obviously,
that was the toughest one.
>> I just feel bad, though, you
know.
I'm sorry.
I let my teammates down today.
James tried to eat that balut as
slow as he possibly could so
that I could keep up with him.
But unfortunately, I just could
not get that down my throat, so
we ended up on the losing end.
>> Perfect plan, genius idea,
smashed.
And so we're trying to look on
the positive side and say, "Hey,
we lost."
We still get rid of one of the
old Zhan Hu, and we still have
our numbers.
Courtney's on our side for sure.
I'm positive, almost positive
James is on our side.
>> Yeah.
>> Because he did try to throw
that.
And I don't think he has
anything going on with the new
guys.
>> No, I don't think so.
I think he's... seriously, I
think he's with us.
>> He's with us.
>> I really do think he's with
us.
>> We've got five right there.
And I'm almost 100% positive
that Frosti will stay.
Right now we need him to trust
us and this tonight will help
him trust us.
Does that make sense?
Because we want to trust him
just as much as he wants to
trust us.
>> I'm also coming to get water.
>> Oh, good.
So Sherea is gone tonight.
>> Right.
>> All right, so we're in
agreement for Sherea tonight,
huh?
>> Yeah.
>> So after Todd's and Amanda's
plans went awry, they're like,
"Okay, well, no question about
it, we're voting off Sherea,
okay?"
Sherea, Sherea, Sherea.
And I'm like, "Yeah, okay,
whatever."
But when I thought about for a
little while, I actually like
Sharea.
And if it came down to it of who
I thought would vote me out
quicker, I definitely think that
she would keep me around longer
than Jean-Robert.
>> Well, right now, the people
at Fei Long want me to go home.
What they don't understand is
they need to be scared of the
people in their tribe, too.
You know, as far as Jean-Robert,
he'll vote any of them out.
So the same time they're looking
at me, they need to be scared of
each other.
Mm-hmm.
>> You know, everybody's name
gets on the list eventually.
I mean, I hate doing it, I
really do, because I like her a
lot.
I hate it.
>> I do, too.
>> Obviously, I'd rather it be
her than me, and I think it's a
smarter move.
>> Do you know what I mean?
>> It's the smarter idea right
now to stick with more of our
tribe.
And honestly, it has to be
Frosti or Sharea.
>> Do you know what I mean?
>> No, I totally understand.
>> Eventually, it will be down
to like, our people, you know?
But right now, it's not.
And we have to look at the
bigger picture of things.
>> The thing is, it's like, our
great plan didn't work today
either.
Do you know what I mean?
>> There's only so much planning
we can do at, like, every stage.
Like, you can't predict what's
going to happen.
>> I like to trust my gut and my
vibe, and so far, I've really
felt comfortable about my
position in the game.
All of a sudden, something
doesn't feel 100% to me.
The plan was either Sherea or
Frosti, most likely Sherea.
But I've got to tell you, I'm
uneasy right now.
>> I feel like we should vote
out Jean-Robert tonight.
Do you know what's happening
now?
We are lining ourselves up as
power players.
They will get rid of us if we
don't start doing what people
want.
Because Jean-Robert is not
stupid, and he will turn on us.
He will.
>> Sharea will too.
Todd, I don't know.
I think Jean-Robert definitely
has to go.
I don't think now is the time,
honestly.
>> I don't know what to do.
>> Honestly, my gut feeling is
that...
>> My gut's saying Jean-Robert.
>> So I guess it comes down to
who we feel we can trust more at
this point-- Jean-Robert or
Sherea.
>> I... this sucks.
>> JEFF: Well, when you're
winning, it's easy to get along.
You start to lose, things
change.
Sherea, what did you sense when
you guys got back today after
losing?
>> I sense a lot of shadiness
today.
You know, people talking like,
"Let's talk here.
Okay, now let's talk.
Let me go talk.
I'll be back."
That's how it's running over
here, you know?
>> JEFF: Jean-Robert, does the
game continue to change day to
day, and does that then affect
the way you play it?
>> I'll tell you what-- it's day
18, Jeff, and I'm a changed
person.
I mean, I find myself doing a
little cooking, a little fire.
And it's routine now.
It's not even chores.
>> Did you ask him all that?
Wow.
Somebody along the way told him
that he had something important
to say, because he does a lot of
talking, always running his
mouth, story after story.
>> What do you say to that?
>> You don't say anything.
That's why you don't say
anything to me, because you know
you don't want me to say
anything back to you.
You talk to the people who
aren't going to say anything to
you.
Little do you know, they don't
like you.
>> JEFF: Would that surprise
you, Jean-Robert, if you found
out that the people on the tribe
didn't like you?
>> I'm certain that some of the
people do not like me.
I'm a bad boy.
Sometimes that happens.
But, you know, even as a bad
boy, and being aggressive, I
like the way I'm playing this
game, and I think I'm doing just
fine.
>> JEFF: Courtney, the look on
your face, very smug.
>> Bad boy?
Not quite the term I would have
perhaps selected.
But it's always interesting to
hear people talk about
themselves and, really, "Bad
boy, bad boy," because you play
poker or something?
Do you have a Harley I don't
know about?
>> JEFF: Would a Harley make
Jean-Robert a bad boy?
>> Well, I mean, bad boy... who
do you think you are, Luke
Perry?
>> JEFF: How would you describe
Jean-Robert, Courtney?
>> I mean, we don't get along.
We don't like each other.
I think he walks around, he
talks a lot, jokes that aren't
funny, lot of judgments of other
people, a lot of self-
righteousness.
You know, I think, like, that
kind of stuff is, like... he's
just a crappy person.
And, yeah, I'm going to laugh at
him when he's like, "I'm a bad
boy, but, you know, I go out and
get some fish."
Like, it's just funny, just as
an observer and to being like
sort of the outsider of my
tribe.
Like, I know we have two members
of another tribe that have
joined us, but I think I was on
the outs before they got here.
>> See, that kinds of hurts,
though, because I love you, and
I've love you since day three,
is what I say, because day one
and two I didn't really like
you.
>> But...
>> I love you, and we get along
so well.
>> I love you guys, too, but
it's also... you know, it's a
really cliquey tribe.
>> And I click well with you is
how I felt.
And so, like, for you to say
that you're on the outskirts and
that you're not close to me is a
little bit of, like, rubbing
salt in the wounds.
>> But...
>> I guess that's just how it
is, though.
>> I got to tell you, Jeff, even
with this infighting going on,
and this is a place to air out
dirty laundry, when it comes to
the challenges and coming
together, I think we really do
work well together as a team.
And to be honest with you, we're
in a good spot.
I like where we're at.
>> JEFF: On that note, it is
time to vote.
Denise, you're up.
>> It's unfortunate we didn't
get a chance to know each other
a little better.
>> Somebody along the way told
you you were hot.
I'm going to bust that big
bubble you call a mouth and tell
you you're not.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, J.R, Jean-Robert.
Jean-Robert.
Two votes Jean-Robert.
Sherea.
Two votes Jean-Robert, one vote
Two votes Jean-Robert, two votes
Sherea.
That's three votes Sherea, two
votes Jean-Robert.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: China, Sherea.
That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Sherea, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
Jamie and Erik make a discovery.
>> It looks idol-ish.
>> I want to be friends with
you!
>> JEFF: Todd struggles to held
his alliance together.
>> I don't feel like you're my
friends.
>> If I get screwed, I'm going
to hold you responsible.
>> JEFF: Drop your buffs.
>> Oh, my god!
>> The fact that the Fei Long
people decided to stick together
because of numbers, you know, it
just says that they're getting
played.
They'll realize it sooner or
later, and I hope half of them
get screwed, since some of them
screwed me.
But, you know, they knew they
couldn't beat me in the
challenges.
I was the strong one, they were
the weak ones.
So of course they're going to
take out the threat.