>> JEFF PROBST: 36 days ago, ten
fans of Survivor were pitted
against ten of their favorite
players from seasons past.
>> You could be a fan of the
Boston Red Sox, man, but you
don't want to play against the
Boston Red Sox.
You're going to get your ass
handed to you.
>> JEFF: Let's get it on.
The tropical paradise of
Micronesia...
>> Got a big old four-foot
shark.
>> JEFF: ...proved to be both
bountiful and brutal.
The castaways were unexpectedly
battered by storms on a daily
basis.
>> You watch this show at home,
and when they show the rain,
they show it for, like, 30
seconds.
They're not showing that you're
standing in the rain for five,
six hours straight.
>> JEFF: The conditions were so
harsh that one castaway quit.
>> I can't be here one more
minute.
I can't take it.
>> Bye.
>> JEFF: Throughout the game,
injuries piled up like never
before...
Our injury tally so far, Penner
has a busted-up knee, Parvati
has a busted-up lip, Ami has a
tweaked knee.
...forcing out two of the game's
strongest players.
>> I can only recommend, for the
sake of his leg and his life,
that he leaves the game now.
It's not going to get better.
>> Oh, god bless it.
>> JEFF: Let's get you out of
here and get you to a hospital.
It was the first time ever that
three players left without being
voted out.
But the game continued.
An early alliance was formed
between Amanda, Parvati, and
Cirie.
>> All right, ladies, I have
both of you guys' words that
it's us three to the end.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: The three women stayed
true to each other throughout
the entire game, but Parvati
made some side deals on her own.
>> I might just go ahead and
pull in Natalie and Alexis and
take them with me and Amanda and
Cirie.
Everyone else, they're dead to
me.
>> JEFF: All the women banded
together to form a super-
alliance which took control of
the game.
>> What is the plan?
>> Final five girls.
>> JEFF: The first thing on
their agenda was to blindside
the biggest threat.
>> This is, like, the perfect
opportunity to get rid of Ozzy,
because he'll never see it
coming.
>> JEFF: He had the hidden
immunity idol, but he didn't
play it.
Ozzy, the tribe has spoken.
But Ozzy's exit was just the
beginning.
>> It's like the black widow
brigade-- all the girls spinning
the guys around as much as we
can until they don't know which
way is up, and then we're
devouring them one at a time.
>> JEFF: What happened next was
an unprecedented series of
blindsides.
Jason had the idol, but the
women convinced him that he was
safe.
Jason.
So he didn't play it.
At the following tribal council,
because Erik had immunity, the
women were forced to vote out
one of their own.
They picked Amanda.
>> Pretty much everyone here has
told me they're voting for me
tonight.
>> JEFF: But when she produced
the hidden immunity idol...
>> I got it!
>> JEFF: ...the vote bounced
back to Alexis.
Alexis, you need to bring me
your torch.
And when Erik won immunity
again...
>> Nat, tell him if he were to
give you the necklace that would
redeem him, and we would vote
for Amanda.
>> Who would fall for that?
>> I want to give individual
immunity to Natalie.
>> JEFF: ...they pulled off the
biggest blindside in Survivor
history.
>> You officially go down as the
dumbest survivor ever.
>> JEFF: Erik, the tribe has
spoken.
Three days left in this game.
Who knows what is going to
happen?
Now four are left.
Cirie...
>> In this game for me, it's all
about who I think I can trust.
And if I feel that I can trust
you, then I'm willing to go all
the way with you.
But if I don't trust you, then
you can't believe a word I tell
you.
>> JEFF: ...Natalie...
>> I'm in game mode, and now I'm
actually having a lot more fun.
I'm getting to be more of
myself, which is proving to be
pretty ruthless and pretty
stone-cold bitch, and pretty
cutthroat.
>> JEFF: ...Amanda...
>> This is where the game gets
interesting.
This season I have developed
more personal relationships than
I did in China, and this game, I
played completely loyal and just
fought my way to the end.
>> JEFF: ...Parvati.
>> Coming back and playing
really aggressively, and pretty
much no holds barred for me.
So I haven't been here miserable
going through all this crap to
not win this game.
>> JEFF: Find out tonight who
will outlast all the rest to
become the sole survivor.
>> ♪ Final four, final four
final four, final four. ♪
>> When Erik paused, I was
like...
I know.
And I was like...
And he goes, "Well, this is
risky."
And I was like, "It's in the
bag.
It is in the bag!"
Everyone has fallen into our
trap.
Everyone.
And it's the same trap over and
over and over again.
And every single person keeps
falling into it.
>> When I wrote his name down, I
said, "My mama always told me
you might not be able to beat
them with these but you can
always beat them with this."
We couldn't beat Erik at
anything.
But now that's all taken care
of.
Erik's somewhere having a
sandwich, and we're going to
continue with the game.
>> That's four back-to-back
blindsides which you girls have
managed to evade every single
one of them.
>> Wow.
>> Like, let's see what happens
next.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> There she is.
How long have you been up for?
>> I don't know.
Probably an hour.
>> Did you sleep good?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> We were talking about Erik.
>> Oh, it's just tearing my
heart out that there aren't any
guys around here.
Can't you see the tears in my
eyes?
>> These guys just walk right
into the Venus flytrap, and they
get eaten alive.
>> Yeah.
>> Heist number four...
>> In a row.
>> ...goes off without a hitch.
>> I'm going to check and see if
my money is still in my pocket
around y'all.
I can't trust you.
I'm nervous around y'all.
>> I'm nervous around you.
>> Oh, my god!
That's so many!
Nice job, Parv.
>> I haven't missed the guys
here for one second.
I love having this group of
girls here, Just chilling,
hanging out, without the big
egos running around and the guys
trying to, you know, provide and
look cool in front of the
ladies.
I love just me and the girls.
>> This has been a really hard
season.
>> It's been so hard.
>> Because all the freaking
girls are smart girls in this
season.
>> I'm not kidding.
And we beat them out with our
brains.
I can't believe we beat those
guys.
>> Oh, my god.
I'm just so thankful to be here.
>> I'm so thankful that you're
here.
I feel like you have a way of,
like, convincing people, and
they're like, "You're so right."
You really should... you really
should swallow your pride and
ask for whatever you want all
the time.
>> I know.
I feel I live out of fear in my
normal life a lot.
I'm so scared of people saying
no, so I don't ask.
>> Yeah.
But your life could be so much
better if you just ask for
things that you want.
>> I know.
>> You know?
My position at this point, I'm
the only fan left.
They're all favorites.
They all started on a tribe
together.
But I've definitely made a
personal bond and connection
with Parvati.
We get each other.
We have great conversation.
So I think we complement each
other well.
>> Honestly, I think the people
that you encounter when you do
things like this, like, the
people that you're with, you
have to know that they are there
for a reason.
>> Yeah.
>> You know?
And there's a reason that you
and I are here together.
We have a one-in-four shot of
winning a million dollars right
now.
>> Yeah.
>> Unbelievable.
>> But everyone here has earned
their spot in the final three,
you know?
>> Absolutely.
>> Everyone here has played a
damn good game.
>> Yeah.
I think Parvati is an ally for
me in this game.
My conversations and my heart-
to-hearts with Parvati and our
great connection-- does it
benefit me at all if we're
closer than not?
Of course.
>> Tree mail!
>> What does it say?
>> Yeah, I was hoping for food.
>> Me, too.
>> Reward or immunity?
Does it say?
>> "Indeed you've accomplished a
noble task.
You've made it the final four.
To climb the heights of victory,
you need to scramble once more."
>> What?
>> It's immunity.
Today?
>> Wow.
>> I am not happy.
>> We're thinking that winning
this challenge is pretty much
guaranteed final three.
So we have to beat Natalie.
I mean, we love the fact that
it's all women, but being that
it's all women, one of us has to
go.
>> JEFF: Four ladies feeling oh
so good about themselves.
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yep.
>> JEFF: First things first.
Natalie, I'll take back that
necklace.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
start on a very small perch at
the top of a 20-foot pole in the
water.
On my go, you will use a bucket
to gather water that you will
then pour into a bamboo chute.
As the water fills up the chute,
it will raise a set of keys.
You'll take those keys, you'll
swim back to shore and use them
to unlock a chest containing 16
individually shaped ladder
rungs.
The first person to correctly
assemble their ladder, climb to
the top, and raise their flag,
wins immunity, guaranteed a one-
in-three shot at winning this
game.
Make sense?
>> Yep.
>> JEFF: We'll draw for
position.
We'll get started.
Here we go, for immunity and a
guaranteed spot in the final
three.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Going to pull up that bucket
full of water, and then pour it
down that bamboo chute.
The more water you get in, the
faster you will raise those keys
up to where you can grab them.
Natalie having a lot of success.
Parvati got most of it in the
chute.
Doesn't matter how fast you pull
up the water if you don't pour
it in the chute.
Natalie doing a great job.
Can't quite reach her keys.
Parvati and Natalie neck and
neck right now.
Natalie has her keys.
She's in the water.
Parvati very close.
Parvati reaching for her keys.
Parvati unclips.
She's in the water.
Got to get to shore and open
that chest.
Amanda reaching for those keys.
Can't do it.
Going to take another bucket of
water.
Natalie and Parvati with a big
lead at this point.
Both opening their chests up.
Amanda has her set of keys.
Got to unclip.
She's in the water.
Cirie, is it close enough?
Cirie reaches for the keys.
Cirie has her keys!
Get in that water.
Everybody is in this.
Natalie continues to extend her
lead.
This ladder will take some time
to assemble.
Only one person going to walk
away from here with immunity.
The other three vulnerable at
tonight's tribal council.
You have 16 ladder rungs.
Each ladder rung is individually
shaped and will only go into one
slot on that ladder.
If you have to force it, it's
not right.
If you have a lot of play, it's
16 different options, but it
only goes together one way.
Amanda appears to be making some
progress.
Parvati's got some rungs in her
ladder.
Natalie and Cirie trying to make
sure they're right.
Merely getting to the top is not
enough.
Amanda making a lot of progress.
If she's right, that's a big
lead.
Parvati skipping up ahead.
Putting some of the higher
ladder rungs in first.
Cirie is working her way up
methodically from the bottom.
Natalie having a little trouble
with this puzzle.
Amanda pulling away from the
pack.
At this point, it is Amanda's
challenge to lose.
She has a huge lead.
Amanda can't get that last rung
in.
Something's not right.
Amanda going now rung by rung
trying to figure out where she's
off.
Natalie getting closer.
Amanda swapping pieces out.
Immunity so close.
Amanda thinks she has it, and
she does.
Amanda wins immunity!
>> Good job, girl.
>> Good job.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Good job, girl.
That was tough.
>> JEFF: Amanda, come on over.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> JEFF: Guaranteed a one-in-
three shot at winning this game
and the million bucks that goes
with it.
Natalie, Cirie, Parvati, after
37 hard-fought days, one of you
will not make it to the final.
Figure out who that's going to
be tonight at tribal council.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you at tribal.
>> The only reason you beat me
is because your legs are longer
than mine.
>> Right.
>> Me, too.
>> I was right hot on your
trail.
>> Oh, I know, girl.
>> We all were.
>> I'm in the final three.
I can't believe it.
I'm really, like... I'm
ecstatic.
And that's, like, twice in a
row.
And this time I have played my
game so different, and I feel so
much better about it.
>> We could set Gloria free.
>> You know, they always talk
about the lowest man on the
totem pole.
I do indeed feel like the low
woman on the totem pole.
But am I just going to tuck my
tail between my legs and scurry
out of here and say, "Bye, guys,
well, it was great, I'm going
home"?
No, I'm going to explore all my
options.
If Gloria is anything like the
women on this camp, she'll mate
with that dude and then rip his
neck off.
>> Oh, that's funny.
>> I'm dealing women who are as
smart as I am.
So if I go in and I'm hustling
and I'm shaking and I'm moving
and I'm stressing, they're going
to see right through it.
So I think if I'm calm, cool,
and collected there's a way to
weasel in and communicate with
them in a way that may seem
reasonable.
>> This sucks.
I hate when it gets to this
point.
Why can't we all just stay?
Why can't they have a final
four?
>> That would be cool.
>> I don't know, Natty, girl.
I don't know.
Have you promised anybody your
vote?
Oh, good.
>> No.
>> Good.
>> I believe Cirie is quite
nervous as far as jury votes are
concerned.
I could use this to address
Parvati to help me out.
It's kind of a little glimmer at
the end of the tunnel, a little
light, because I do firmly
believe that Parvati would go
out on a limb for me.
>> Huh?
>> How good of a shot do we have
to win this, do you think?
>> Huge.
>> Yeah?
>> You and I?
I think it's between you and I.
>> Really?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Definitely.
>> It's been kind of our plan
from pretty much the beginning
to have me, Parv and Cirie in
the final three.
But I think Cirie is definitely
a threat as far as swaying
votes from the jury one way or
the other.
And I don't want Natalie to go.
I think, you know, she
definitely deserves to be here.
I think she's played a good
game.
Cirie, she knows that if Natalie
would have won, Nat would have
voted with me and you and Cirie
would have been gone.
>> True.
>> I don't know who I'm voting
for tonight.
I mean, it's hard.
It's far in the game.
You know, it's not easy.
You know everyone is still
playing the game at this point.
It would be stupid not to still
be playing the game.
>> I give Natalie so much
credit.
>> Me, too.
>> Cirie got lucky to be with
us.
>> Yeah.
>> You okay?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I was like...
"No.
You're asking me this right now
because..."
>> I love Natalie to death, and
I think she's a lesser threat as
far as jury votes than Cirie.
And now the time has come where
it's, like, I could switch it up
now, and then we have our
biggest jury threat out of the
game.
But, seriously, in this game,
and how this game's been played
all these women are so crafty, I
wouldn't put it past any single
one of us to work some kind of
deal out and make it to the
three.
>> Yeah.
>> I could be going home
tonight.
They could have made a deal with
Natalie and decided, "You know
what?
We like you better.
Cirie's out."
And smiling in my face.
I saw their work already.
We duped so many people....
>> ...with straight faces.
>> JEFF: We'll now bring in the
members of our jury.
Eliza, Ozzy, Jason, James,
Alexis, and Erik, voted out at
the last tribal council.
So we have a final four
consisting of only women.
And all of you women have been
involved in another first-- four
straight blindsides.
Natalie, after the performance
from the four of you at the last
tribal council, you all should
be nominated for a Survivor
Academy Award.
It was masterful to watch.
>> No disrespect to anyone, but
it went down seamlessly.
We achieved an impossible task.
So it was a great feeling.
>> JEFF: So after four straight
blindsides, what's the feeling
going into tonight's vote?
>> I think at this point, the
four of us respect each other
enough that I don't think there
would be a blindside.
I would pray for a blindside on
some level.
Like now it would actually
benefit me better than all the
other four.
>> JEFF: Amanda, how concerned
are you tonight that you know
exactly what's happening?
>> At this point, Jeff, I have
no idea what's going on.
I mean, how many times does a
blindside have to happen before
you figure out that you know
nothing about what's going on at
all?
I'm fairly confident that I know
what's going to happen tonight,
but I can't be certain.
>> JEFF: Parvati, it seems to me
only a fool would say anything
with confidence at tribal
council.
All you have to do is look
across at Ozzy, and Jason, and
Alexis, and Erik.
They were all certain they
weren't going home.
>> Yeah, I think this has been
the craziest, messiest, most
strategic game in the history of
Survivor.
So for anyone to feel confident,
it's ludicrous.
But I can't read anyone's mind,
and I don't know what anyone
else is thinking but myself.
>> JEFF: Amanda, have you guys
talked about, "What do we do
when there are only three people
left?"
Or have you been assuming,
"That's all I've got to do is
just get to final three and I'm
good to go"?
>> No one here, I think I can
honestly say that, is expecting
a final two.
At this point in the game, it
would take us for another
whirlwind.
>> JEFF: Cirie, how would it
change the game if you knew it
was a final two?
>> I mean, it is nerve-wracking
to think it could be a final
two, because that makes me feel
like, once again, I'm on the
bottom of the alliance, which is
not a good place to be, Jeff.
>> I just have a question-- when
did you ever think you were on
the bottom of the alliance?
>> No, no, no, from the five,
when I started with you, Ozzy,
James, and Parvati, basically,
it's unspoken that I'm on the
bottom.
Ozzy wanted you four to be in
the final four.
So where does that place me when
we're going to the five?
That makes me fifth.
>> I'm talking about after the
merge.
Like, when have you felt on the
bottom?
>> Always.
>> Always?
>> Between us three?
It's obvious, because not one
person in any alliance has ever
said, "I won't vote for Cirie."
You have said, "I won't vote
for" certain people.
She has said, "I won't vote for
you."
So that clearly places me at the
bottom of the alliance.
>> I'm just wondering.
>> And I'm explaining how I feel
that way.
I would be foolish not to think
that.
>> JEFF: Natalie, you're holding
back a big grin.
>> I think at this point,
anything's an opportunity.
You know, I'm just letting them
duke it out, and may the best
woman win.
>> JEFF: All right, let's get to
the vote.
Amanda, you have the immunity
necklace, you're not planning on
giving it to anyone else, are
you?
>> No.
>> JEFF: You cannot vote for
Amanda.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Cirie.
Natalie.
One vote Natalie, one vote
Cirie.
Natalie.
Two votes Natalie, one vote
Cirie.
14th person voted out and the
seventh member of our jury,
Natalie.
That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Natalie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, once again you have
survived the vote and made it to
the final three.
Congratulations.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> I have to say that I am
pretty happy with the way that I
played the game.
I was the last fan standing.
And I feel proud of the group of
girls they finished with.
I respect the way that you guys
played the game with me.
So thank you.
>> That was a weird tribal
tonight, wasn't it?
>> I don't think I've ever been
so exhausted in my entire life.
>> You and me both.
>> What am I doing?
>> You were trying to make us
look so awful at tribal.
>> How?
You asked me how I think I'm on
the bottom of an alliance, and I
explained to you every single
alliance that I've been in how
I'm on the bottom.
>> That's bull( no audio )
Just be real.
>> How is it bull ( no audio )?
That's not game.
That's real facts.
That's exactly what this is.
I should be...
>> Because in the five, how are
you on the outs?
>> Because you're snuggled up
over there with James, she's
snuggled up over there with
Ozzy.
Most of the time y'all four are
together.
If you were me, what would you
feel?
I mean, be me for a minute.
And because I said it out loud,
you're upset?
With this alliance with y'all
two, she told me she couldn't
vote you.
So that makes me at the bottom
of this alliance.
Have any one of you ever said,
"I can't vote Cirie out?"
>> How do you know?
>> Yes or no?
I'm asking you.
>> How do you know?
>> Have I talked to you about
final two?
I feel that I've been at the
bottom of every single alliance.
>> I just don't see that, and I
haven't seen that.
I haven't seen that the whole
game.
>> You're not me.
You're not me.
That's why you can't see it.
>> I can't understand you when
you're screaming at me.
>> Okay, I'm not screaming.
>> Thank you.
>> I can't explain it any more.
I don't know how else to say it.
>> Yeah, I know.
I mean, it makes sense.
>> I know.
I'm sorry.
>> I'm sorry for yelling at you,
but don't...
>> No, I know.
I'm just...
>> ...accuse me of stuff that
I'm...
>> I wasn't trying to accuse
you.
It came out very badly, and I'm
sorry.
I'm just on my breaking point
right now.
>> I know.
>> You have two more days.
>> Let me give you a hug,
because this is pitiful for us
to make it this far and then you
be...
>> I know, I'm sorry.
>> No, it's all right.
It's all right.
>> I didn't mean it like that.
I just kind of broke down and I
started yelling at Cirie about
stupid things that I don't even
know why I yelled.
And it's...I feel like I've been
doing this forever, you know?
Straight from China, I come
here, and it just... I just
can't take it.
I almost lost it when Jeff
mentioned that there might be a
final two, and I lost it.
>> Oh!
>> There's no way it would be a
final two.
There's no way.
>> Yeah, don't say that again,
Parv, because you've been wrong
every time.
You don't comfort me by saying
that.
It's been the plan from day one
for Parvati, Amanda, myself to
be final three, and it would
just break my heart to find out
it's going to be a final two.
So I want to celebrate, but
there's, like, that hint in the
back of my mind-- don't get
falsely happy and then find out
this is not the end of it.
>> It's the final three.
Everybody just needs to chill
out.
>> Did you find a machete?
Because all that yelling makes
me thirsty.
>> 38 days.
I really don't think I will ever
touch a coconut again.
>> We need a tree mail here.
>> Relax.
>> I am ecstatic to be here in
the final three with these two
girls.
At least we assume it's a final
three.
It's been a long road, and we
feel very blessed to be here
with each other.
Come on out.
>> Come on, Gloria.
>> We're celebrating by setting
our mascot free, Gloria.
She's our last chicken standing.
>> Get out of there!
>> Yay!
>> Uh-oh!
Rather than try to kill Gloria
and have her flopping around
in misery, we decided we can not
eat.
We only have a couple of days
left.
Let Gloria go.
She might not leave here.
This is her home.
She's making a nest to lay the
damn egg.
>> Unfortunately, Gloria doesn't
want to leave camp.
She's, like, hanging around.
She's like a pet dog now.
I guess she doesn't realize that
this is over.
It's a done deal.
>> We're the craftiest survivors
of all time, to be modest.
>> Nice.
Nice.
>> What is it?
It doesn't look like food.
>> No.
>> What?
Oh, my...
>> It looks like a challenge.
Freaking paddle.
All right.
"Congratulations, final three.
You have done what 17 of your
fellow tribesmen and women could
not.
Today you will honor their
memories before proceeding to
your final immunity challenge.
Get into your boat and head out
to Exile Island.
There you will find the torches
of your fallen comrades.
Reflect upon them as they each
had a part in getting you to
this point.
You'll then proceed to your
final immunity challenge."
>> Oh, my god.
>> Wow.
>> My heart just dropped.
>> All right, let's go, ladies.
>> We got tree mail today, and
we thought there was going to be
like, food, you know, for the
final three.
And it's another immunity
challenge.
It's like, when is it going to
end, you know?
Like, there's only so much you
can take, and then someone has
to leave now, like, after
everything.
I am so tight with these girls.
Like, this just sucks
completely.
>> It's never ending.
>> I feel sick.
>> Me, too.
The fact that it's a final two
and not a final three was almost
poetic.
I mean, we've been blindsiding
people left and right, and
essentially we got blindsided.
We thought we had it made.
I guess, you know, what goes
around comes around.
>> Okay.
...regroup, get it together.
>> One more time.
>> I need to regroup.
Now we have to kick it back into
gear and get ready for this
immunity challenge today.
And for me, it's taken me down a
peg.
Like, I feel a little bit
humbled.
But I think the rites of passage
will give me a little
perspective, because it's a
chance for us to honor everyone
that we fought so hard to beat,
and I think we all want to give
those people credit for being
such strong competitors and for
not making it easy on us.
>> I can't feel bad.
Look how far I made it.
I mean, we started out with 20
people.
And they were all hard-core
players, and would love to be
here right now.
So I want to tip my hat to them
and say, you know, "Good job.
I beat you, but good job."
>> Oh, thank god.
He was actually kind of a decent
guy while he lasted.
Let's do it.
>> I consider myself the
cerebral assassin of Survivor.
And I'm not going at 100%, I'm
not playing.
So, you know, to go out on my
own terms, I kind of protected
the legacy of Jonny Fairplay.
So I'm very happy with that.
>> Oh, Mary.
Didn't really know Mary.
>> That's probably the worst
thing that could ever happen to
somebody on Survivor, is being
one of the first people voted
out of your tribe.
Maybe I was a strong player and
they saw me as a threat, but I
really felt like just a ton of
bricks hit me, and game over.
>> Yau-Man.
Cirie's fiercest competitor.
>> That's only reason he had to
go so early is because he was
such a great player.
>> When I first walked in and
someone said that I'm one of the
most likable players, I think
that pretty much sets me apart
as a big target.
Also, my problem, I know, is
that I don't have that, you know
killer instinct to go up against
some of these other people.
But even though I got voted out
so early, it's still quite a fun
experience.
>> Oh, Mikey.
>> Good old Mikey B.
He was a fierce competitor.
>> It hurts.
It hurts to get sent home that
early in the game.
I was having fun out there, and
I just wanted to continue to
fight.
But it is a life-changing
experience.
And it reminds you that life is
good.
>> Joel.
The big guy.
>> Truck was pretty intense.
>> That's exactly the words
I was going to use.
He was intense.
>> I went in with the goal to
play the game hard, and I feel
like I did that.
But my Survivor experience
should be summed up as failure.
My goal was to be there at the
end.
And I didn't reach the goal.
I failed.
>> Jonathan, Jonathan, Jonathan.
>> Jonathan is a smooth talker.
He was tough, though, in this
game, man.
I give him props.
>> Yeah, he wouldn't have quit
for anything.
>> Nothing.
>> If he hadn't been taken out
on medical, he never would have
quit.
>> That's so sad.
>> Leaving the game for medical
reasons, I was able to leave
with my head held high, no
animosity towards anyone, and
there's nothing that I could
have done about it.
It is something extremely
special, and I'll always hold
this near and dear, and this is
a once-in-a-lifetime experience
I got to do twice.
>> Oh, Chet!
>> My buddy.
>> You know, I have to say the
chickens have not been the same
since Chet left.
>> My Survivor experience was
something I only dreamt of
happening.
Even though I was told I was
going out first I went out
seventh in a beautiful way, as
far as I'm concerned.
Everybody who was praised for
their strength, praised for
their agility, praised for their
athletic ability, I outlasted
them.
>> I loved Kathy.
>> She was...
>> She was a colorful character.
>> Yeah, to say the least.
>> I am in awe of every person
who's ever played the game of
Survivor.
It's the most difficult thing
I've ever done.
Childbirth, I thought that was
tough.
Nah.
I'd rather whip out eight more
kids in ten minutes than ever do
this again.
That's how much harder
Survivor is.
>> Oh, Tracy.
>> She was... you know, I think
she was underestimated in this
game as a physical competitor.
>> Even if it's 20 days, 20 days
may seem like not a lot of time
to a lot of people, but when the
rain is hitting you for nine and
a half hours, you just can't be
that same person any longer
because you have just you and
the elements.
I am not the same person any
longer.
And I don't think I ever want to
be again.
>> Ami, Ami, Ami.
>> You know, I loved Ami.
>> I did, too.
Ami loved everyone.
>> This game, I was so much more
sensitive than I was the first
game.
I've learned the balance for me
of vulnerability and strength.
Of walking into a situation and
being strong with who I am, and
knowing that I don't need the
feedback of other people to know
I'm okay with who I am.
>> Oh, Eliza.
My arch rival that I had to
compete with for 22 days.
>> Wow.
>> Eliza put up a good fight in
this game.
>> Oh, yeah.
The last tribal council...
>> She went down...
>> She went down swinging.
>> ...in a blaze of glory.
>> Yes, she did.
>> I was the underdog.
I was on the outs almost from
the start, because I didn't
really have an alliance with
anyone.
And so I knew that I was on the
bottom, and trying to work every
angle, which is my game, which
is the only game I know how to
play.
And I think I did a good job.
>> Ozzy!
>> Oh, Oz!
>> I think he's the most well-
rounded player ever in Survivor.
>> And you like him.
>> That's why he had to go.
>> You can carry his torch.
I'll let you carry it.
>> To a certain point, your time
out in Survivor does define you
to a large degree.
It's like a chance to really
search your soul and get to know
who you are, and what you're
made of.
I knew that I had to trust
people this time around to make
it anywhere, and that was what
ended up being my downfall.
But my relationship with Amanda
was worth more to me than any
amount of money.
>> Good old Jason.
>> He gave Ozzy a ride for his
money, too.
>> He beat Ozzy twice.
>> I came out here as a strong
competitor and a good provider,
and nobody really saw that
because I think everybody was
just focused on Ozzy.
So it's a bit comforting knowing
that Ozzy and I both went out in
the same way.
It shows that I'm just as good
of a competitor and provider as
Ozzy.
>> Oh, James, my little cuddle
bug.
>> He was honest.
>> Yeah, he was a straight
shooter.
>> I'd much rather have been
voted out, because it's like,
closure.
With a finger injury, it kills
me.
But the trials I had to go
through with them girls really
was quite a test.
I mean, I'm not a bully, but I
surely don't like anybody
telling me what to do.
So, I mean, I really had to let
go and go within myself to calm
down.
>> Alexis.
>> You know, if, Alexis made it
this far, she would definitely
be hard to beat.
>> Yeah, Alexis was a charmer.
>> Yes, definitely.
>> I felt like I always had this
kind of split between, like, the
super-competitive tomboy, but
then the super-nice southern
hospitality girl.
So in a weird way, I feel like I
came into this game a little
girl and I got to grow up and
left a woman.
>> Poor Erik.
I'm sorry he had to be the
victim of the women's wrath.
But play with fire, you'll get
burned.
>> I don't think you can play
this game without changing as a
person.
I mean, I've seen so much in so
few days that I've never, ever
seen in my life.
I've seen these women here, and
they are vicious.
I mean, they are cutthroat.
They are very tough, and there's
a lot of strength in them.
And it's opened my eyes a little
bit about the way that women are
and the way that they operate.
>> Natalie.
>> Aww.
The last fan in Survivor.
>> Good on you, girl.
>> Good on you, baby.
>> If the woman has the
opportunity to think, she will
outwit a man.
They may outbrawn a woman, but a
woman will definitely outwit a
man, hands down, every time.
I think I learned a lot about
myself, and right now, I'm kind
of my biggest fan.
>> JEFF: Welcome to your final
immunity challenge.
You ready to get to it?
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: All right, Amanda, I'm
take back the necklace.
For the last time, immunity is
back up for grabs.
For today's immunity challenge,
you each have a long wooden
cylinder that has been cut into
several pieces.
In the center is a slot on which
rests a metal ball.
On go, you'll pick up the first
piece using two handles,
balancing the ball.
Every five minutes, as the
challenge continues, you will
add more pieces, making it more
difficult to hold on to.
If at any point the ball drops,
you're out of the challenge.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, is guaranteed a spot
at the final tribal council,
where you will get a chance to
convince the jury you're worthy
of a million dollars.
Also at tonight's tribal council
you will, in effect, be deciding
who you want to sit next to you
at that final tribal.
A very big decision.
This is potentially a million-
dollar challenge.
Shall we get to it?
All right, everybody pick up
your handles.
Five seconds that I count you
down, that is your grace period.
Use these five seconds as free
time to get your bearings.
When we get to one is when we
go.
Everybody's picked up their
handles, got your first piece in
place.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This challenge is officially on.
We'll go five minutes before we
start adding more pieces, and
when we do, it will become much
more difficult.
The slightest lapse in
concentration, and you will be
out of this challenge.
You have to constantly check in
with yourself and make sure you
are staying focused.
All right, this round is over.
You can set them down.
You are safe.
All right, let's add two more
pieces, making this cylinder a
little longer, a little more
difficult to hold.
Everybody grab your handles.
Here we go.
Everybody lift.
Five, four, three, two, one.
We are on.
Everybody now holding three
pieces.
Concentrate.
All of your energy should be
focused on keeping that ball
stable.
You drop this ball, it could
cost you a million dollars.
One more minute left in this
round.
You can do it.
Hang in there.
Don't blow it now.
Last 15 seconds in this round.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This round is over.
You're safe.
Set it down.
Nice work.
All right, let's add two more
pieces.
Now it's going to get
interesting.
Everybody pick up your handles.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This round is on.
After 38 days of playing this
game together as a team, nowhere
left to hide.
Now, instead of working
together, you have to battle
against each other with only one
goal-- beat the other two.
Parvati drops her ball.
Parvati is the first person out
of this challenge.
Parvati's fate is no longer in
her own hands.
We are now down to Cirie and
Amanda.
15 seconds left in this round.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This round is over.
Set it down.
You are safe.
>> Oh, my god.
>> JEFF: All right, next round.
Let's add two more pieces.
Every time you add pieces, it
gets more difficult.
Let's put your handles up.
This could be the round that
decides it all.
Here we go.
Five, four, three, two... Cirie
drops.
If it falls off while I'm still
counting, we reset.
Take your time when you're
lifting it up.
It's not a race.
Here we go, five, four, three,
two, one.
Challenge is back on.
Amanda going underhand this
time.
Cirie sticking with the same
grip.
Wherever you're holding it, do
not move it.
Hold that ball steady if you
want a shot at a million bucks.
You have very little wiggle
room.
30 more seconds, and you move on
to the last round.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This round is over.
You're safe.
Set it down.
All right.
Last and final round.
Add the last two pieces.
Pick up your handles.
This round will go until
somebody drops their ball.
Here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one.
We are back on.
This is the final round of this
challenge.
Everything you have inside you
should be focused on keeping
that ball stable.
The person left standing after
this, immunity.
Shot at a million bucks.
You lose this challenge, your
fate is not in your hands.
Cirie loses her concentration.
Amanda wins final immunity and
is guaranteed a spot at the
final tribal council.
>> Good job, babies.
You're awesome.
>> Thank you.
>> Good job.
You're awesome.
>> I love you guys.
>> JEFF: Amanda, come on over.
No better time to have this than
right now.
>> Yep.
>> JEFF: With this, you are
guaranteed a spot at the final
tribal council.
You will get a chance to
convince the jury you are worthy
of a million bucks.
At tonight's tribal council, you
will cast a vote, and in doing
so, you will vote either Parvati
or Cirie out of the game.
The other person you're going to
take with you to the final
tribal.
Big, big decision.
Have a fun afternoon.
Head back to camp.
I will see you guys at tribal.
>> Oh, Gloria.
>> She likes it here.
She likes the coop.
>> Yeah.
We just got back from the last
immunity challenge, and I won
immunity.
So I'm going to the final two.
And it's either Parvati or Cirie
going home tonight.
Honestly, this is the hardest
decision I've had to make this
whole game, because, you know,
we're each close.
All of us are close.
So who do you send home?
>> I don't know what happened.
I must have blinked.
>> And it just fell?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> She's a closer, that one, you
know?
>> I thought for sure that I
could win this one.
Because during surgeries, you
have to hold, like, retractors
or instrumentation, and you
can't really move.
If you move, somebody might get
hurt.
Unfortunately, Amanda won.
And since Parv and Amanda are so
buddy-buddy, unless something
happens, I'm probably going home
tonight.
>> This is my decision, pretty
much.
>> I know.
We're not even voting, I don't
think.
>> No, I am.
Me.
>> Yeah.
>> That sucks.
>> I know.
I mean, she understands.
My fate is pretty much in
Amanda's hands right now.
But I'm fairly confident that
she's going to take me to the
final two with her.
We've had an alliance since day
one out here.
And we also have a really tight
relationship, Amanda and I,
that's developed over the course
of this game.
So I'm not worried about it,
really.
This is good, because then
tomorrow we can just help each
other with our opening speeches,
just question each other and
hang out.
Oh, today was awful, though.
>> Well, you've been handling
all these situations really
gracefully, you know.
>> Well, I already knew, like,
if I didn't win that she'd take
you, so it's not like...
>> She pissed way more people
off than I did.
>> Yeah, actually, huh?
>> Yeah.
>> This is such a nightmare that
this happened today.
I can't even believe that... how
do I make the decision?
What do I go by?
>> I don't know.
>> It's, like, the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
>> Yeah.
>> Parvati and Cirie both
deserve to be here.
They both want to be here.
So I honestly don't know what to
do.
I have a really good personal
relationship with Parvati, so I
feel more loyal to Parvati.
>> I feel like your best shot
with the jury is taking me over
Parv.
Every person she screwed over, I
screwed over.
We did everything together.
Every blindside we orchestrated
together.
Most of them I did most of the
talking for.
>> So how is...
>> Yeah, but that's only if the
people are willing to listen.
These are the people I screwed
over I would have to talk to.
>> Cirie has pissed a lot of
people off on the jury.
Probably more than Parvati.
But Cirie is a hell of a
speaker.
She can convince anyone to do
anything.
And in the final tribal council,
she could convince the jury to
give her the million dollars.
So, I mean, it's kind of a
catch-22.
>> It should be interesting.
>> Making this decision tonight
is killing me.
You kind of have to just go with
how you feel, and a gut feeling.
And I've been going with my gut
this whole game, and it's gotten
me this far, but I know that
this decision could cost me the
million dollars.
>> JEFF: We'll now bring in the
members of our jury.
Eliza, Ozzy, Jason, James,
Alexis, Erik, and Natalie, voted
out at the last tribal council.
Well, after 38 days, we've
reached a point where there is
only one decision left to be
made before we turn this game
over to the jury.
And that is, who's going to that
final tribal council?
Amanda, after winning today's
immunity challenge, you are in
total control.
>> I know.
>> JEFF: Tough decision, in a
way.
You guys have been together
almost from the beginning.
>> Yeah.
I mean, winning immunity today
was a blessing and a curse at
the same time.
You know, it's a blessing
because I'm guaranteed the final
two, and it's a curse because I
have to choose who goes with me.
And we're so close, it's...
It's just a hard, hard decision.
>> JEFF: Cirie, do you buy that
it's difficult for Amanda?
>> Yeah.
I believe it's difficult for
Amanda, because we have been
together since day one.
Amanda, Parvati, and myself, we
kind of decided, you know, it
should be us three 'til the end.
And it pretty much has been
that.
>> JEFF: Parvati, difficult to
not have any say at this point?
>> I honestly don't envy
Amanda's position at all right
now.
I mean, she has a hard decision
to make.
We have all been protecting each
other through blindside after
blindside, weathering storms
together, and I don't think it
is going to be an easy decision,
and I wouldn't want to be making
it.
>> JEFF: So Amanda, take me
through both sides of this.
What about bringing Parvati or
Cirie to the end is risky?
>> You know, with these girls
it's a tossup at this point.
Strategy-wise, Cirie is a great
talker.
She can convince pretty much
anyone to do anything.
And, you know, that's a threat
at the end of the game.
And Parvati has played a very
social game.
She has made personal
relationships on the jury that I
think will definitely come into
play at the final tribal
council.
So it was a hard decision, but I
ultimately made a decision on my
gut feeling.
>> JEFF: Take me through the
mixed emotions that have to be
going through your head-- the
joy of knowing "I succeeded,
I am going to be at the final
tribal after 39 days of
working," and the pain of having
to vote somebody out that you've
been with from the beginning.
>> Yeah.
>> That's okay.
>> It's just really hard for me,
because I feel like either way,
it's a lose-lose situation for
me at this point.
I mean, if I go with Cirie, I'm
hurts Parvati.
If I go with Parvati, I'm
hurting Cirie.
I know that this vote tonight is
going to hurt someone's
feelings.
And I'm just having a hard time
with that.
>> JEFF: All right, let's get to
the vote.
Amanda, since you have immunity,
nobody can vote for you.
That means Cirie can only vote
for Parvati.
Parvati can only vote for Cirie.
Parvati and Cirie, you won't
vote tonight.
The only person voting tonight
is Amanda.
You'll be voting out the 15th
person from this game, and you
will be deciding who you are
bringing with you to the final
tribal council.
If you're wrong, it is a
million-dollar mistake.
If you're right, this time
tomorrow night, you're a
millionaire.
>> I know.
>> JEFF: It's time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
I'll go get the vote.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the vote.
15th person voted out, and the
eighth and final member of our
jury, Cirie.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> I'm sorry.
>> It's okay.
It's all right.
Cirie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> JEFF: Parvati, Amanda, you
have gone as far as you can go
in this game.
The power now shifts to the
jury.
Eight people-- including Cirie--
that you had a hand in voting
out now hold your fate in their
hands.
You've got one more night.
I hope you can enjoy it.
I'll see you both tomorrow night
for your final tribal council.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> Here I am again, coming up
just short.
HB, John, Jamil, Jared, Mom,
Dad, sorry.
I tried my hardest.
It just wasn't meant to be.
>> We're going home tonight.
>> I was so happy when I woke up
today.
To finally know that I made it
to the end, you know, I just
kind of, like, breathed and...
I can't believe we did this.
>> I can't believe we're the
last two.
>> I know.
Everyone's gone but me and you.
>> We bamboozled everyone out of
the game.
>> This morning when I woke up,
I think the happiness, like,
started in my stomach, and it
bubbled up, and I couldn't wipe
the smile off my face.
All the hard work has paid off.
We're here, and it's done, and
we're final two.
>> Oh, my god!
>> BOTH: Oh...
my...
God.
>> Amanda and I pretty much own
this game.
She made it all the way to the
end in China.
I made it almost all the way to
the end in the Cooks.
To be in the final two in this
season, it's a serious
accomplishment, and I feel like
I can stand up tall and be like,
"I am a survivor."
Oh, my god.
I am so glad I'm with you.
>> I know, me, too!
There's no other person here I'd
rather be here with right now.
>> Me, either.
This is, like, the prettiest
picnic ever.
>> This is, like, a huge
accomplishment.
Like, this is the biggest
accomplishment of my life.
>> Mine, too.
>> I feel like we battled every
element to get where we are
right now-- like, every possible
thing that we could go through,
we've gone through, and we've,
like, mastered it, and we've
gotten ourselves here.
In the past six months, I've
been living in the jungle for 78
days, you know, so I don't think
there's much in real life that I
can't handle after
two Survivors in a row.
>> We're going to be so good
tonight at that tribal thing.
>> Oh, yeah, we're going to be,
like, happy and full and be
like, "Yeah, ask us your
questions.
Bring it on."
>> "Bring it on, bitches."
>> I think it's interesting that
me and Parvati are in the end of
this game together, because we
have played completely different
games.
I think I have played this game
loyal to my alliances, and
Parvati pretty much did anything
she needed to do to take
control.
And because of that, a lot of
people on the jury don't like
her, so that could be a benefit
for me.
>> We have had this game in the
palm of our hands since we met.
And then the switch-up.
And then the craziness.
And then, still, it's still you
and me.
I really, honestly, feel so
relaxed going into the final
tribal council.
I feel like I've played a game
that's been very true to myself.
I don't feel like I could have
played this game better.
>> You want to do the honors?
>> Sure.
>> Ah-hah!
My game was a lot more
aggressive than Amanda's game.
It was a lot more cutthroat,
more cold-blooded.
I was playing this to win.
>> We're pyromaniacs.
>> That's awesome.
I think my strongest point I can
make tonight is standing up and
owning that I have been a
powerful, controlling player
throughout the duration of this
game.
>> Parvati has played a
cutthroat, aggressive game, and
I know that she's going to
finish with a cutthroat,
aggressive game, and that could
be by her throwing me under the
bus tonight at tribal.
And if that is the case, then I
am ready to fight for this.
I think people will give me
their votes, because I was loyal
to every alliance that I've
made.
Yeah, the jury makes the
decision, but ultimately, it's
me and Parvati convincing the
jury what to do.
Tonight we're going toe to toe,
and one person is going to win a
million dollars, and the other
person is going to walk away
with nothing, and may the best
woman win.
>> JEFF: We'll now bring in the
members of our jury.
Eliza, Ozzy, Jason, James,
Alexis, Erik, Natalie, and
Cirie, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Welcome to your final tribal
council.
Congratulations on outlasting 18
other people in this game.
Tonight, the power shifts from
this side of the tribal council
over to the jury.
Based on what they've seen over
the last 39 days and what they
hear tonight, the jury will make
a million-dollar decision.
Here's how it's going to work.
You will each get a chance to
make an opening statement.
This is your first chance to
convince this jury why you are
deserving of the title of sole
survivor.
The jury will then get their
first chance to address you.
We will then vote.
Opening statements.
Amanda, you're up.
>> I came into this game, you
know, wanting to do two things.
I wanted to play a loyal game,
and I wanted to fight
physically, strategically, and
mentally to the end.
And, you know, I'm really proud
of how I played.
And I know I wouldn't be sitting
here without, you know, help
from all of you.
So thanks.
I wanted to say thanks.
>> JEFF: Parvati.
>> I came into this game with a
previous reputation from the
Cook Islands as the flirt.
I knew that I had to play so
much differently than I played
in the Cook Islands.
Like, I had to play
aggressively.
I had to beat my competition
before my competition had a
chance to beat me.
And you gave me a serious run
for my money, all of you.
So the only thing I could do was
make bold power plays, and with
the help of a powerful group of
women, pull off some of the
hugest heists in Survivor
history.
So ask me anything you want, and
you'll get an honest answer.
>> JEFF: All right, jury, in a
moment you're going to get your
first chance to address Amanda
and Parvati.
I'll give you a moment to think
about what you want to say.
>> JEFF: All right, jury, it is
now your first opportunity to
address Amanda and Parvati,
trying to gain the information
you need to make a million-
dollar decision.
Eliza, get us started.
>> Both of you played a great
strategic game.
You made moves, and I can
respect that.
But I honestly have no idea who
I'm going to vote for tonight.
Parvati, all 24 days I spent in
this game I spent on the island
with you.
I think taking out Ozzy was a
brilliant strategic move.
I respect that move that you
made.
What I can't respect, however,
is everything you did that was
not necessary for strategic
advancement in this game.
You talked about me behind my
back.
You made fun of me.
And that is not what got you to
the final two.
It leads me to believe that you
might just be a mean person.
So I'm going to have a lot of
difficulty giving you my vote
tonight.
Amanda, you played a great
strategic game, and it was very
impressive.
However, listening to you talk
literally made me want to kill
myself sometimes.
I don't know that I can vote for
someone who I think is so
superficial.
And I'm going to be sitting
right there tonight listening to
every single thing you both say,
because my vote is absolutely
not determined.
So I hope that I can see some
genuineness and honesty from you
two tonight.
>> JEFF: Thanks, Eliza.
Jason, you're up.
>> Amanda, when Ozzy was voted
out, if you were let in on that
plan, would you have told Ozzy?
>> Yes.
>> And Parv, I've had these
misconceptions of you as a
devious, manipulative player.
And I just want to know what
some of your redeeming qualities
have been in the game.
>> Okay.
Well, I think for one, I was
very protective of my alliance
with Cirie and Amanda, gave them
my loyalty, and was loyal to
them all the way to the end.
So protectiveness and loyalty to
the ladies that I gave my
loyalty to.
We didn't kill Gloria the
chicken.
We saved her life.
So I'm an animal lover.
Is that good enough?
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: Satisfied?
>> Yeah.
Good luck to the both of you.
>> JEFF: Alexis, you're up.
>> My first question is for
Parv.
And, obviously, one of the
biggest, most important things
to me is how passionate I am
about working with young girls.
I guess I'm just really curious
what makes you a better role
model than Amanda for young
girls.
>> I don't know if it's better
or worse.
I'm more outspoken than Amanda.
So I think I'm more independent.
I don't like things to be done
for me.
Amanda would go along with the
flow, and for me, I think I'm
more willing to put myself out
there and make bold moves.
And I didn't see much of that
from Amanda.
So I guess that's why I feel
like I would make a better role
model.
>> Thank you.
Amanda, I have seen a bunch of
Oscar award-winning performances
and we couldn't help but be
laughing when you were crying
about sending Cirie home.
It's not that I'm not
sympathetic to it.
It's just I think, you know, you
cry wolf so many times that,
like, what about, if any, part
of your game has been genuine?
>> I haven't been faking
anything that I've done at
tribal.
The tears... like, I've only
cried the last tribal council,
and that was genuine.
Like, that was the hardest
decision I've ever had to make.
I didn't come here trying to get
sympathy votes.
I don't want sympathy votes.
>> JEFF: Do you have what you
need?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> JEFF: Okay.
Natalie, you're up.
>> Ladies.
First of all, you have my
respect tonight, woman to woman.
I'll start with you, Parv.
You have labeled yourself as a
flirt.
You're probably the most
masterful person in the history
of Survivor to play the flirt
card, which is great.
My question to you is how does
that resonate for you in the
bedroom?
How do you take that to the next
level as far as strategy in the
game?
How does that translate your
layers of being?
>> JEFF: Come on, guys.
Parvati, do you know what she's
asking?
>> You're a flirt.
You flirted with me on several
occasions.
I'm not complaining.
>> You're sexy.
>> Thanks.
So how does being the flirt
parallel to your intimate life?
>> I think my strategy in this
game has been infused with my
personality, and being
flirtatious is a big part of my
personality.
At home, it gets me what I want.
I'll flirt with girls to get my
way, or I'll flirt with guys to
get my way.
And I think I honestly can
develop genuine relationships
with people without flirting
with them.
But it is an old standby, I'm
not going to lie.
>> Okay.
Amanda, clearly, you're a
beautiful woman.
You appear to be a very strong
woman.
Unfortunately, you always had,
like, a glazed-over look on your
face.
I did notice that.
My question to you is was that
your strategy to kind of play
the zombied pretty girl, not
really knowing what's going on,
pageant queen cliche, or is this
who you are as a person?
>> No, it's neither.
It was neither my strategy, nor
do I think that's who I am as a
person.
I'm a strong woman.
I definitely have substance.
Sometimes I'm a little reserved,
but I definitely think I've made
intellectual strategic
decisions.
And, you know, I want to compete
with the men.
Like, I came in this game to
compete with the guys.
And I don't want anything given
to me.
I came in here to earn
everything.
>> Okay, thank you both for your
answers.
>> JEFF: Thanks, Natalie.
Erik, you're up.
>> Hi, girls.
Let me just start by saying five
to six days ago, I would have
been 100% voting for Amanda in
this situation.
I mean, I really respected you,
Amanda.
And I really thought of you kind
of as a big sister, or a cousin.
As of late, after seeing certain
things, I mean, I'm looking at
you right now with a lot of
questions.
I felt totally burned, totally
thrown under the bus at the past
two tribal councils that I was
there.
You pretty much ripped me apart.
I mean, on what basis did you
have to just judge me in front
of everybody, in front of this
jury?
>> Okay.
>> I just want to know that.
I really want to know that.
>> You know, everything I said
in tribal council was honest.
You were unloyal to me, and you
tried to get me voted out, and I
was hurt.
I wasn't going to sit there and
let you try to vote me out and
just keep my mouth shut.
I'm sorry, if I hurt your
feelings, but...
>> Too late for "I'm sorries."
I've heard you say that... you
said that directly to me at one
of the tribal councils.
Too little, too late.
You said that directly to me.
And now you're going to say "I'm
sorry" to me.
I really don't buy that at all.
>> Okay.
>> I think I'm good.
>> JEFF: Okay.
James.
How's the finger?
>> The finger's all right.
It's good.
I mean, I'm not even going to be
difficult.
Amanda pretty much knows she's
got it in the bag.
The only thing is, Parvati, you
fluffed me.
You did the great move with
Ozzy, and the next day you came
up to me with a bunch of fluff.
So we're just going to pretend
like you didn't say that, have a
go again, we reenact it, you
give me a different version.
Go on, give it to me, and make
it believable.
>> Ha, ha, got you, sucker.
What?
>> That's not it.
Try a little bit harder.
>> That is what you wanted me to
say.
>> No, that's not what I wanted.
>> That's exactly what you said
you wanted me to say.
>> You're over-exaggerating it.
What I wanted, you to just be
honest.
"Hey, I'm playing the game.
It's a game."
I mean, when I play the game...
>> It is a game.
And the game... the motto is
"Outplay, outwit, outlast."
>> Exactly.
>> There was no chance for me to
win this game if I stuck with
you, and if I stuck with Oz.
There was no chance of me
sitting here if I stuck with you
guys.
And that's what I felt.
I felt like I had to make that
move when I made it.
It also, you know, gave me a lot
of control.
And that's what I wanted.
>> Are you finished?
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> JEFF: Cirie, you're up.
>> All righty.
Congratulations to both of you.
I'm going to start with you,
Amanda.
Being that you had the decision
to make, tell me and the jury
why Parvati deserves a million
dollars more than I do.
>> Parvati played a very
aggressive, bold game.
I think she's stood by her game
the whole time, and I respect
that about her.
>> So in saying that, are you
saying you don't respect my
game?
>> No, I respect your game as
well.
I think Parvati made bolder
decisions in this game.
>> Than I did?
>> Yes.
And I think she was kind of the
powerhouse in making those
decisions happen.
>> Okay.
Parvati, I would like you to
tell the jury why I should be
sitting in your seat, and you be
over here on the jury.
>> I think you played a pretty
brilliant game.
Yours was a little more, you
know, under the radar than mine
was, which I think is a great
strategy, you know, to get up
here, too.
But I can't compete with a
mother of three.
You have kids.
You have a family.
I don't have that.
So based on those two factors, I
would say it should have been
you right here.
Is that good?
Is that good enough?
No?
>> I'll ponder over here.
>> Okay.
>> Thanks, ladies.
Good luck.
>> Thanks.
>> JEFF: Thanks, Cirie.
Ozzy, you're up.
>> I think I might be the
biggest idiot up here.
I am truly to the bottom of my
heart hurt by what you did to
me.
It was a great move.
It really was.
But I never in a million years
thought that you could do that
to me.
You put a price on our
friendship.
You threw us away like garbage.
You basically said, "You know
what?
You're not quite worth this much
money."
And it hurts, you know?
It really does hurt.
And how can you say that you're
a role model when you're willing
to discard a valuable friendship
like that?
A human being.
But I don't want words.
No words at all.
I don't want to talk to you.
Honestly, the hardest part for
me was the fact that you took
away 14 days that I could have
spent with Amanda.
Amanda, when I told you on the
beach at one point when you
asked me if I was playing you or
not, I told you honestly that
I'm not faking it.
I'm not faking my feelings for
you or anything, no.
I really am having feelings that
I've never really felt before
and have never...
I honestly feel like I started
to fall in love with you.
And... I don't know.
You're just an amazing girl.
And I really want everybody to
know that.
And I'm glad I didn't win Cook
Island so that I could be here
and have met you.
>> Thank you.
>> And that's it.
>> JEFF: All right, jury.
You've now had your opportunity
to address Amanda and Parvati.
Certainly, an interesting final
tribal council, very emotional
at times.
Now you have to make a
million-dollar decision.
Who do you vote for to win this
game?
I'm going to give you a moment
to think about your vote.
>> JEFF: All right, jury, Amanda
and Parvati have had their
chance to address you.
You've had your chance to
address them.
Now we get to the vote.
Tonight you are voting for a
winner-- the name of the person
you feel most deserving of the
title of sole survivor, and the
million-dollar check that goes
with it.
For the last time, it is time to
vote.
Cirie, you're up.
>> I'm willing to forgive and
forget if you're willing to
forgive and forget.
You played a good game.
>> I love you so much, girl.
You absolutely deserve this.
And I know you're going to do
amazing things with this money.
>> I hope to god that you win.
You deserve it a million times
more than Parvati.
And... love you.
>> Oh, my god.
>> JEFF: I'll go get the votes.
Amanda, Parvati, jury, thank you
for a great season of Survivor.
I will see you back in the US
For the reading of the votes.
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: Thank you!
Let's get to it!
( cheers and applause )
All right.
Have a seat.
( cheers and applause )
Hello.
All right, let's get to this.
Amanda, Parvati, jury, I've got
to say, word on the street from
Survivor fans is that aside
from our first season, this is
perhaps the best season we've
ever had.
( cheers and applause )
So kudos to you guys.
Now it's time to put it to bed.
There are eight votes tonight.
It takes five to win.
I will read the votes.
>> Parvati.
>> I know who wrote that.
>> JEFF: One vote Parvati.
Amanda.
One vote Amanda, one vote
Parvati.
Two votes Parvati, one vote
Amanda.
We're tied.
Two votes Amanda, two votes
Parvati.
>> I like that.
>> JEFF: Three votes Parvati,
two votes Amanda.
We're tied again.
That's three votes Amanda, three
votes Parvati, two votes left.
Parvati.
Here's where we stand.
Four votes Parvati, three votes
Amanda, one vote left.
If this vote is for Amanda, we
have a tie.
If this vote is for Parvati, we
have a winner.
The winner of Survivor: Fans
Versus Favorites, Parvati.
( cheers and applause )
>> You just won a million
dollars!
>> JEFF: Head on down to the
family, Parv.
>> I love you
I voted for you.
>> Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
Captioned by