>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
On day 22, a merge brought the
two tribes together.
>> Eat, drink, and embrace your
new tribe.
>> JEFF: And five out of the six
remaining favorites rekindled
their alliance.
>> I'm on the same page with
James and Parvati and Ozzy and
Amanda.
>> JEFF: But Parvati formed a
side alliance with fans Natalie
and Alexis.
>> I've put us in an alliance
without you being there.
I'm in an alliance with everyone
on the island.
I'm going to have a decision to
make.
>> JEFF: After the merge, Jason
and Eliza were the clear
targets.
>> I think both we annoy people.
>> JEFF: So when Ozzy was beaten
by Jason at the immunity
challenge...
Nice work.
...Jason gave Eliza what he
thought was the hidden immunity
idol.
And at tribal council, Eliza
played it.
This is not a hidden immunity
idol.
>> That means Ozzy has it.
Jason found it on Exile.
Ozzy has the real one.
>> JEFF: And she was voted
out...
Eliza.
...making her the first member
of the jury.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Jason, what happened?
What just happened?
>> What do you mean?
>> Did you give her an idol?
>> Who gave her an idol?
>> Jason did.
>> That was my only shot at the
game.
So my plan of trying to send
Ozzy home failed.
I'm glad that Eliza played the
hidden immunity idol instead of
myself.
I would have hated to play the
idol and then actually go home
looking like even more of a
fool.
>> Ozzy found it.
>> It was a decoy.
>> Yeah.
I took a lesson from Yau-Man.
>> Eliza whipping out that phony
hidden immunity idol so
matter-of-factly and looking at
all of us like, "Ha!"
And I'm probably like... my
heart is going... for a minute I
was a little bit nervous.
Like, I thought Ozzy had it, but
just a slim chance that she
might have had it.
Ozzy would have been gone.
The idol would have been played.
Might not have been such a bad
thing.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Ozzy fooled me.
He did a good job.
I felt kind of silly, but, you
know, in the end, that's not
what matters.
It's how far you get in the
game.
And to go up against Ozzy in the
first individual immunity
challenge and win let me know
that, you know, Ozzy's not the
only godlike competitor who can
play this game.
You know, I feel like I could
fare pretty well as long as I
keep continuing to beat Ozzy.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: For today's challenge,
you will divide into two teams
of four.
On my go, one person from each
team will swim out into the
water and crawl through a
multilevel net tunnel.
When you reach the platform,
you'll study a collection of
Micronesian symbols, then race
back to the start.
You'll then place as many of
those symbols as you can on your
answer board in the same
positions as they are on the
platform.
Then the next person goes.
To make it a little more
complicated, you will have extra
pieces which will not match
anything.
Once your team thinks the board
is right, let me know.
If you're wrong, somebody has to
go out again.
First team to place all their
symbols correctly wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: The winning team of
four will fly to one of the most
cultural places in Micronesia,
Yap.
You'll enjoy a local dance, a
local feast, and you will spend
the night in a traditional
Micronesian bai, typically
reserved for chiefs and other
dignitaries.
>> Wow.
>> JEFF: You'll return to camp
in the morning.
Worth playing for?
>> Absolutely worth playing for.
>> JEFF: Because we have nine
people and we're dividing into
two teams of four, there will be
one extra person.
The person not chosen will not
participate in the challenge,
and will instead go to Exile
Island.
>> Oh!
>> JEFF: We're going to draw for
captains.
We'll do a schoolyard pick.
All right, Jason's a captain.
Natalie's a captain.
Natalie, Jason, rock, paper,
scissor to see who chooses
first.
>> On three.
>> Yep.
>> One, two, three.
>> JEFF: Jason won the rock,
paper, scissor.
Jason, make your first move.
>> Okay, come on over, Ozzy.
>> JEFF: Jason choose Ozzy.
Natalie, you're up.
Who do you want?
>> James.
>> JEFF: Jason, your pick.
>> Eric, come on over.
>> Natalie, who is your next
choice?
>> Parvati.
>> JEFF: Parvati joins James and
Natalie.
We're down to three.
Jason, your pick?
>> Amanda, come on over.
>> JEFF: All right, Natalie, one
choice left.
It's Alexis or Cirie.
The person you do not choose is
going to Exile Island.
>> Alexis.
>> JEFF: Alexis joins Natalie,
James, and Parvati.
All right, Cirie.
>> Bye, y'all.
Have fun.
>> JEFF: You will return to this
game at the next immunity
challenge.
All right, we have our two teams
of four.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize, we'll get started.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Jason and Parvati out first.
Into the water, and through the
net tunnel.
>> Go, baby, go!
>> JEFF: Jason flying over it.
Jason in the water swimming to
the platform.
>> Go, Parv!
>> JEFF: Jason studying those
symbols.
Trying to remember as many as he
can.
Parvati now on the platform.
>> Take your time, girl!
>> JEFF: Jason heading back.
Parvati heading back.
If you call it and you're wrong,
somebody else has got to swim
out before you can make any
changes.
>> Let's go, let's go!
>> JEFF: Jason screaming through
that tunnel on the way back.
Parvati right on his tail.
>> Good job, girl!
>> JEFF: Jason first back to the
answer board.
Parvati back to the answer
board.
Not only do you have to remember
the symbols you saw on the other
board, you have to differentiate
between the fake pieces.
Parvati's done.
Alexis heading out.
Jason taking his time on that
board.
Ozzy heading out for the orange
team.
Alexis out for the purple team.
>> Go, Ozzy!
>> JEFF: Ozzy flying through
that tunnel.
Ozzy and Alexis studying the
symbols.
Ozzy heading back for one.
Alexis still studying.
Ozzy back to the answer board.
>> All right, you got this!
>> JEFF: Alexis back for purple.
>> Good girl!
>> JEFF: Ozzy putting in a lot
of pieces.
>> Don't worry, Alexis.
Just focus.
Remember those symbols.
>> JEFF: Ozzy finishes his turn.
Erik now out on the course
Alexis really taking her time,
trying to be right.
Alexis finishes her turn.
James heading out on the course.
Erik to the platform.
James to the platform.
Erik and James both coming back.
>> Come on, James.
>> JEFF: James finished with his
turn.
Natalie now out on the course.
>> Go, Nat.
>> JEFF: Erik finished with his
turn.
Amanda is heading out on the
course.
Amanda is to the platform.
Natalie heading back for purple.
Amanda studying those symbols.
It is better to be right than
fast.
>> Good job, Nat.
>> JEFF: Natalie back to the
answer board
>> You got it, girl.
>> JEFF: Remember the answer key
and the finished answer board
have to match.
>> Come on, Amanda!
Come on, Amanda!
>> JEFF: Amanda throws herself
over that net tunnel.
>> Come on, Nat.
You've got this.
Just focus.
>> Amanda, switch out that white
one.
>> Hurry, please!
>> Good job, Nat.
Bring it home for us.
>> JEFF: Both teams think
they're close.
>> Call it!
>> That right?
>> JEFF: No, you're wrong.
Somebody's got to head out and
figure out what's wrong.
>> Take out the first one, the
very first boat.
>> First boat?
>> That one, yeah.
And put the one with the light
sky.
I think that's it.
>> Amanda, comes back.
>> JEFF: Orange thinks they have
it?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Orange wins reward!
>> JEFF: Amanda, Ozzy, Erik,
Jason, nice job.
You're going on reward.
Alexis, Natalie, Parvati, James,
got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
All right, guys, you are going
to board a plane.
Fly correctly to Yap.
You'll enjoy a little culture, a
little food, get a break away
from camp.
Congratulations.
Enjoy.
Head on out.
>> This is awesome, guys.
>> Yeah.
>> It was great to get a reward
with Ozzy, Erik, and Amanda.
I was really excited.
Right now, we're on our way to
Yap.
I'm sitting here in the copilot
seat.
Hopefully I won't have to take
over or anything, but, yeah, I
think we're all ready here for a
great adventure.
>> Yap is a little island nation
all by itself in the middle of
the Pacific Ocean.
And I've never even heard of
Yap, but a lot of people haven't
heard of Hickney where I've
grown up, so I kind of relate to
that little tiny country.
>> Oh!
>> Hello, and welcome to the
village.
>> Hello.
>> My name is Francis.
>> Thank you, thank you.
This jungle is very primeval,
and there's little stone
walkways that are worn away by
thousands of feet that have
walked on them.
And in the middle of the jungle,
there's a village.
>> Oh, my god!
>> This village looked out of
time.
It was almost like this village
had been there for millions of
years.
I was expecting a dinosaur to
come out of the woods, kind of,
( imitates dinosaur )
>> Oh, my god.
I can't even believe how much
food is on this table.
>> Oh, my god.
One of everything.
>> I'm, like, in heaven right
now, pretty much.
>> Isn't this amazing?
>> This is beer.
>> Thank you.
>> Yes, yes.
>> See, that's the tree.
>> Oh, they're climbing it!
>> Oh, wow.
I've never seen anything like
this in my life.
>> Yeah, it's incredible.
It's absolutely incredible.
>> Cheers, you guys.
Erik, cheers.
>> Give it, give it!
>> Oh!
>> I thought it interesting that
all their women were topless.
I'm sitting there ready to eat
my foot food, and the lunch lady
doesn't have a shirt on.
Oh, my gosh.
It was a little culturally
interesting for me.
I mean, it wasn't a huge deal,
but that's the most boobs I've
probably seen in my whole life.
>> Yeah!
>> ( chanting )
>> One thing that really
fascinated me was the tribal
dance.
It was about some legend about
their culture.
>> ( chanting )
>> They had all the kids in
their village come, and it was
choreographed beautifully.
And I could see that the moms
and the dads were proud of their
kids who were doing it, and it
was really exciting.
It was a very powerful
experience.
>> ( chanting )
>> Yeah!
>> Woo!
>> That was awesome!
>> I really love just going
places with Erik, because he has
this naive, wide-eyed sense
about things.
Erik hasn't really traveled
around too many places in the
world.
So he's really just experiencing
all this stuff for the first
time.
And the innocence that he has,
and the way he really, like,
takes things in, like,
wholeheartedly, it was... it's
wonderful.
Damn it!
>> The men were chewing the
betel nut, which is kind of like
tobaccoish.
So I was kind of hanging out
with them a lot.
They were laughing at me when I
did stupid stuff.
But the betel nut, it relaxed me
a lot.
Maybe a little too much.
Ah!
That night, after much betel nut
and Micronesian beer, I thought,
"Okay, time to call it a night."
And then all of a sudden I had
to rush up, and I pretty much
tossed my cookies on the edge of
the camp.
Oh!
Damn that betel nut!
Beer and betel nut, not a good
combination.
Woo!
What was remarkable about that
was that despite the throwing
up, I really don't regret
anything.
It was all worth it, and I
enjoyed it thoroughly.
Damn!
I'm going to go eat some more.
Oh!
>> It started the most scariest
thunder I've ever heard in my
life.
Just rained all night.
The fire's out.
Pretty cold without the fire.
Just not a good night.
Not a good night at all.
There's nothing to gain by being
on Exile Island.
There's no idol to be found,
because Ozzy has it.
Ozzy's a huge competitor, and
then to have the idol on top of
that, that increased his target,
like, tenfold.
Maybe I'll just have to work on
getting rid of Ozzy and his
idol.
>> The actual gall to get up and
tell somebody something, I mean,
and then lay your ass back down,
that's nerve.
>> Hell, yeah.
>> I know.
>> Hi.
>> Tell us about it, Jason.
Was it the land of milk and
honey?
>> Pretty much.
>> Hey, there he is.
>> What's wrong with you all?
You all look hung over.
>> They had a pig.
They had lobsters.
They had these mangrove crabs
that had a claw, like, almost
the size of my hand.
They had these crazy banana
pancakes.
Four or five different kinds of
chicken.
One with a kind of teriyaki, one
was, like, spicy, one was
barbecued.
>> He's like... everyone else is
downplaying how good the food
is, and he was like, "It was so
delicious!"
Please, give me every mouth
watering detail.
>> She's really close with those
girls, isn't she?
>> Since she's been back since
the swap, we're not so close.
>> I worry about Parvati.
She's put herself into an
alliance with Natalie and
Alexis, and I don't know these
girls.
I don't trust them.
And Ozzy has to be careful,
because he is such a threat, and
they know he has the idol.
And who's to say who's to flip,
who's not to flip?
>> You know, I probably won't be
around much longer unless I
continue to win every single
individual immunity challenge.
>> Yep.
I want to be ready, too.
It'll be life or death for me.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Cirie,
returning from Exile Island.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: First things first.
Jason, I'll take back the
immunity necklace.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to step up on a log.
You're going to raise your hand
above your head.
Your hand will be tethered to a
bucket filled with water.
When your hand drops, the bucket
tips, you get wet, you're out of
the challenge.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, is guaranteed a one in
eight shot at winning the
million bucks.
We'll get started.
All right, everybody is tethered
in.
This challenge is officially on.
>> Oh!
>> No way!
>> This is usury.
>> There's food, I'm out.
>> JEFF: You guys have been out
here a long time without sugar.
>> Ah!
>> JEFF: Big bowl of candy if
you want to get down and give up
immunity.
>> Gummi worms!
>> Gummi worms.
>> Let's go together.
Can we split it, Jeff?
Can we split it if we go
together?
>> JEFF: If you both go down
together, you split it.
>> One, two, three.
>> JEFF: Cirie and Erik opt out
of the challenge for a bowl of
candy.
>> Oh, my god!
You guys.
>> What in the nickelodeon is
going on around here?
>> I'm sorry, you guys.
>> Must go to the happy place.
>> What is it?
>> If it's a steak, I quit, but
if it's not...
>> No!
>> You didn't even wait for him
to ask.
>> JEFF: Alexis got so excited.
No, no.
I hadn't even said what it was.
>> She doesn't get it?
>> No chance.
You got excited.
You're out.
>> ♪ Dum, dum, dum! ♪
>> Alexis, why?
>> JEFF: You can mope and be
mad.
Just so we're clear.
If you want this chocolate chip
cookie and milk, you need to let
me know.
>> Natalie!
>> JEFF: Natalie, did you lose
your concentration?
>> I feel like I'm going to pass
out.
>> JEFF: Natalie is now out of
the challenge.
>> Damn!
>> Sit down.
>> That would suck.
Oh, bitch!
>> JEFF: Lose your concentration
for that long, out of the
challenge.
Nobody interested in the
chocolate chip cookie and milk?
All right.
Four people left-- Parvati,
Ozzy, Jason, and Amanda.
>> JEFF: Next item to try and
tempt you down.
>> It's not that good.
>> JEFF: Three chocolate glazed
donuts.
>> I'll take it!
>> JEFF: Ozzy opts out of the
challenge for three chocolate
donuts.
We're down to three-- Parvati,
Jason, and Amanda.
>> I think I'm done, Jeff.
I have to pee.
>> JEFF: What's that?
>> I think I'm done.
I have to go to the bathroom.
>> JEFF: Amanda's had enough.
You've had enough, pull the
cord.
>> Good job.
>> JEFF: Amanda off for a
bathroom break in the jungle.
And with that, we are down to
two-- Parvati and Jason.
>> JEFF: All right.
You've got a full plate-- three
chocolate chip cookies, four
donuts, big, tall jar of candy,
peanut butter, two chocolate
bars, milk, two beers, and a
huge pizza.
If Parvati steps down or Jason
steps down, you and them will
share all of this.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my god!
>> Jason, you can make friends.
>> If he took one for the team,
we could all very likely say,
"You know what?
We're going to spare him for
tonight."
>> JEFF: Are you saying the
group is prepared to tell Jason
they won't vote him out tonight
if he'll step down?
>> I'd need a guarantee, you
know, that I'm not going home.
>> Who do you want a guarantee
from?
>> Everyone.
>> No.
>> I won't vote you out, Jason,
tonight.
>> One.
>> I will guarantee.
I will guarantee that I won't
vote you out.
>> Two.
>> I'll guarantee.
>> JEFF: So Parvati's the third.
>> I guarantee I won't vote you
out, Jason.
>> I guarantee.
>> JEFF: Alexis, you won't write
his name down either?
>> Yeah.
>> I guarantee.
>> I'll guarantee.
>> I guarantee, too.
>> JEFF: You guarantee.
>> You just got a guarantee from
every person here.
>> JEFF: The question is, Jason,
do you trust them?
>> Yep.
I don't know.
I'll have to think about that
for a moment.
>> You could turn this into
something good.
>> Well, either I'm making the
biggest mistake of the game
right now, or, you know, it
could keep me out here for a
little while longer.
>> Yes.
Ow!
Oh, my god!
>> JEFF: Parvati wins individual
immunity.
>> High five.
>> Good job!
>> JEFF: Parvati,
congratulations.
Individual immunity.
You are the only person safe at
tribal council tonight.
For the other eight of you,
somebody just made a deal that's
going to cost them their spot in
this game.
Go and sit on the bench.
I'll bring you your food.
>> Yay, food.
>> Nice work.
Could you have stayed up there
longer?
>> Probably.
>> I spent six and a half hours
busting my butt trying to win
that immunity necklace, and to
just step down for some food and
people's guarantee that they're
going to keep me around, you
know, I'm taking a chance here.
It could be my biggest mistake
in the game of Survivor, or, you
know, it could be my saving
grace.
>> Wow!
>> I want to thank you guys for
making that happen at the end.
Thank you so much.
>> I think one of the dumbest,
most naive moves in Survivor
history just got played out.
We all guaranteed that we
weren't going to vote for him.
But Jason fell for one of the
oldest tricks in the book, and
he's going to go home.
>> I think six hours up there
made him delirious.
>> Damn fool.
>> This game is outwit,
outplay...
>> Outlast, yeah.
>> I mean, unless you can think
of a better plan.
Otherwise he could still go on
immunity rampage.
>> I mean, I'm pretty sure
Cirie's down.
>> We all guaranteed Jason that
we wouldn't vote him out
tonight.
But I think Ozzy wants to vote
him out anyway, which makes this
the perfect time to get rid of
Ozzy and that idol, because
he'll never see it coming.
Ozzy is like a huge, huge threat
in this game.
So if Jason, Parvati, Natalie,
Alexis, and myself will vote
Ozzy, Ozzy's gone, idol's gone,
clean slate.
>> I'm just going to stand here
for a minute.
I think if I went to the final
five with Ozzy, Ozzy would win
this game.
And I haven't been here,
miserable, going through all
this crap to not win this game.
>> Seriously, good job, Parvati.
>> We'd have to be idiots not to
vote him out tonight.
>> On the other hand, I made an
alliance with Ozzy, and he
protected me in this game a
bunch of times.
And Amanda has been my best
friend since the beginning of
the game.
And James has been my guy since
day one.
So, god, like, what do I do?
>> Ozzy was kind of the one in
charge, and if he's out, it's
really going to shake things up.
But it has to really be kept on
the DL, because if Ozzy gets any
sniff of it, he'll use his idol,
and that would not be good.
>> Do we have to worry about
Parvati, and Natalie, and
Alexis?
>> I don't know.
>> You getting a bad feeling?
>> Yeah.
>> Have you talked to her about
it?
>> No.
>> James is worried about
Parvati.
And this would be a good moment
for someone to try and possibly
flush the idol out, but at this
point, I'm pretty confident in
my alliance.
I mean, hell, this is the reason
why we're favorites.
We played this game before.
We know that once we decide
something we've just got to go
with it.
And it's worked out so far, but
we'll see.
In the last moment I might just
stuff my idol in my bag, and
we'll see what happens at
tribal, and I might end up
playing it just to be safe.
>> JEFF: We'll now bring in your
jury.
Eliza, voted out at the last
tribal council.
All right, Cirie, tell me about
Exile Island.
Did you spend any time looking
for the hidden immunity idol?
>> I mean, I only had two, maybe
three hours of no rain the whole
two days.
So knowing that Ozzy already had
it, why even bother?
>> JEFF: Parvati, is that just a
known fact that everyone
believes, which is Ozzy has the
idol?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, does that put a
target on your back?
>> I mean, of course.
I mean, the idol is a huge thing
in this game.
>> JEFF: Let's talk about
today's challenge-- one of the
craziest things I've ever seen
go down.
Jason, you made a very risky
move.
>> You know, the odds of me
continuing to win the immunity
challenges are very slim.
So I had to give something else
a shot, and it's really just
about crossing my fingers and
hoping these people are going to
stick to their word.
And I can only hope for the
best.
>> JEFF: So James, you guys made
a deal with the devil, in a
sense.
You either stick to that deal
and vote one of yourself out or
you renege on that deal and vote
the guy out you said you
wouldn't vote out.
Either way, the person who gets
snuffed goes to the jury.
Now they're frustrated.
>> You know, just because you
have gotten on everybody's
nerves don't mean a donut is
going to make you better.
You really can't expect to
appease everybody over a donut.
So if you tempt somebody with a
donut, and they say, "Oh, yeah,
sure," they might have just
wanted a damn donut.
>> JEFF: So Cirie, just because
the group gave their word to
Jason doesn't mean the group
will keep their word.
>> Sounds like that what he
said, Jeff.
>> JEFF: Parvati, you're sitting
pretty tonight.
You've got immunity.
What's your take on this whole
deal?
>> I think it was a crazy deal,
but I can kind of understand why
he made the deal.
And if it works out for him,
then that's great for him.
But if he made this deal and he
gets voted out tonight, that's a
huge risk that he took.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, if it's true that
you have the hidden immunity
idol, does that give you a
certain amount of comfort
tonight in an uneasy situation?
>> A certain amount of comfort.
Even then, it's a risk that I
would have to take after all the
votes have been cast.
And at that point I've got to
sort of read the group.
But, yeah, I do have a little
bit of comfort.
>> JEFF: Well, based on what I'm
hearing tonight, either
everybody's going to go back on
their word and Jason is going to
go home, or somebody is going to
get a big surprise.
Let's get to it.
Parvati, you have the
individuality immunity necklace.
You can give it to someone else
if you want.
>> I'm going to keep it.
>> JEFF: You cannot vote for
Parvati.
Everybody else is fair game.
Ozzy, you're up.
>> My vote for tonight is Ozzy.
Hopefully you'll be going home
tonight instead of me.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and they want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to latest tribal council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jason.
Jason.
Two votes Jason.
Ozzy.
Two votes Jason, one vote Ozzy.
Jason.
Three votes Jason, one vote
Ozzy.
Jason.
That's four votes Jason, one
vote Ozzy.
Ozzy.
Four votes Jason, two votes
That's four votes Jason, three
votes Ozzy.
Ozzy.
We're tied.
Four votes Jason, four votes
Ozzy.
One vote left.
Tenth person voted out of
Survivor: Fans Versus
Favorites, and the second
member of our jury, Ozzy.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Thanks, guys.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, that was a very big
blindside.
And that makes things very
unpredictable.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
>> Oh, my god!
I need to do some serious damage
control.
I want to talk to you because I
like you.
I don't want it to be, like,
completely awkward.
>> Oh, it's going to be awkward.
>> I know.
>> If it goes down smoothly, the
girls on this tribe will be
unconquerable.
>> I'm an idiot.
I should have seen it coming,
but I got too comfortable.
I felt like I could trust the
people in my alliance, and it
serves me right.
I'm a fool.
I'm a fool for thinking that.
And to whoever it was in my
alliance that voted the other
way, right now I pretty much
hate you.
So screw you, basically.