>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
On day one, James and Parvati
and Amanda and Ozzy joined
together to form a powerful
alliance.
And later, Ozzy found the hidden
immunity idol...
...and replaced it with a fake
one as a decoy, which was
discovered by Jason.
>> I guess this is the hidden
immunity idol.
>> JEFF: Having the idol put
Ozzy and his alliance in control
of the game.
>> It's in our little four
clique.
And I think it's supposed to be
in our little four clique.
>> JEFF: But their control was
short-lived.
Drop your buffs, we are
switching tribes.
A tribe switch blurred the line
between fans and favorites.
At the new Airai, Parvati formed
a side alliance with Natalie and
Alexis.
>> I hope Amanda will be down
for that when I get back with
her.
>> JEFF: At Malakal, Ami told
the fans that she would join
with them in voting out Ozzy.
>> I'm giving all my trust to
you right now.
>> Okay.
>> Take care of me.
Take care of me, okay, you guys?
Please, because I'm really
sticking my neck out there, you
guys.
>> JEFF: But Erik ratted her
out.
>> Did Ami try and get me out?
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: At tribal council, Ami
desperately tried to defend
herself.
>> I want to be here.
I swear, I'll give you
everything I have.
>> JEFF: In the end, the
favorites didn't believe her,
and Ami was voted out.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Fans Versus
Favorites, Ami.
And for the first time a fan
stayed while a favorite went
home.
>> Good luck, you guys.
>> JEFF: Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Fire, come on.
You're killing me.
Oh, god.
>> I felt bad.
It was just, like, I couldn't
believe what she was saying.
>> The thing was, she dug her
own grave.
>> Here you go.
>> Tonight at tribal council was
hard.
I would have never voted for Ami
ever if she had just been honest
with me, and that's... that's a
key in this game.
You can't be playing all the
sides like that.
If she had just stuck with me,
she'd still be in this game, and
Erik would be gone.
>> I don't understand how she
didn't feel part of our group.
>> How the hell am I still here
today?
I have no idea.
I feel like I'm in this house
that keeps falling down and
somehow I'm, like, making my way
through it as it's breaking
apart.
>> Oh, my god.
>> This was the first time the
favorites have kept a fan and
voted out one of their own.
It feels insane.
>> This tribal council tonight
set a definite precedent on fans
versus favorites in this game.
It's kind of like all bets are
off.
It's kind of every man for
themselves at this point.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> You know that we've severely
pissed off half, at least half,
the jury.
I mean, really pissed them off.
Strangely enough, I think my
closest ally at this point is
Jason, because we're both kind
of on the outs with our tribe.
We both also love this game, and
I think we both annoy people.
I'm not going to lie.
I think that that kind of unites
us, too.
>> Oh, my god.
Jason told me that he had the
hidden immunity idol.
I mean, oh, my god.
It's just crazy.
That puts you in a really good
position.
Jason having the hidden immunity
idol means that it's a good
alliance for me to have, and
hopefully we can take it to the
end.
>> And there is tree mail.
"Malakal, check all of your
personal and tribal possessions
that you may need to survive for
the duration of this game, and
make your way to the location
designated on the map
immediately.
You will receive instructions
when you get there."
>> Oh, my god.
>> We're leaving our beach?
>> We're leaving.
>> We're merging.
>> Yeah, I think we're merging.
>> "Immediately" means right
now.
>> Oh, all right, all right.
>> A merge would be highly
beneficial for me because I
would think I would have more of
a shot at this game, because
there's more players now on the
board to choose from as opposed
to Malakal, which is now four,
and those odds aren't very good
to survive.
And if you want to bring
somebody in or if I want to
bring somebody in, I'll tell you
and Amanda before anything goes.
>> Cool.
>> I owe it to you guys 100%.
>> Cool, thank you.
And I'll be straight up with you
the whole time.
>> That's fine.
One thing that did come out of
last night is rather than being
in opposition to Ozzy, one of
the most powerful players in the
game, I'm now allied with him in
some kind of, like, zookeeper
bond.
Like, I'm more the monkey and
he's the zookeeper now, because
I owe him my life now.
It makes total sense.
Just play it straight up with
somebody that you know.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> "Airai, make your way to the
location designated on the map
immediately."
( cheers )
>> Get the heck off this island.
And I would not ( no audio ) you
all over.
And if we can rely on the four
of us, that would be rad.
>> Oh my god, I am in such a hot
pickle right now.
I have made an alliance with my
original tribe of Ozzy, James,
Cirie, and Amanda.
And the second alliance that I
got myself into is me, Alexis,
Natalie, and Amanda.
So I feel like I have the
numbers on my side no matter
what, but I'm going to have a
decision to make, you know, down
the road.
>> Off to the races, my ladies,
off to the races.
>> Oh, yippee!
The game has really begun, I
feel like.
If Parvati feels more of an
alliance to her original group,
then Natalie and I will be out,
and, you know, that's the game.
But I think right now we're
certainly banking on the fact
that it's not really fans and
favorites anymore.
( cheers )
>> Oh, my god!
>> Glad to see you.
>> Your hair is so fresh.
>> Hey, baby.
>> This is the worst merge I
could possibly imagine.
I was really expecting to see
that Erik was voted out, and
instead it was Ami, who was
probably my closest ally and
closest friend in this game.
And so I feel really alone right
now, and I'm heartbroken that
she's not here.
>> Let's eat!
>> But I'm trying to stay
positive and act like I'm having
fun and try and fit in with the
group.
>> "Tribes, today is cause for
celebration.
You are merged.
You will spend the night here to
eat, drink, and embrace your new
tribe."
( cheers )
"You must decide on a new tribe
name, paint your new tribe flag,
and decide on which of your
former tribe beaches you wish to
live."
>> We're all merged, and we have
to decide what camp to go to.
No question, Malakal, all the
way.
We have everything you need.
I'm kind of mad we had to take
everything down and we're just
going back, but, I mean, I'm so
glad we're going back.
>> They're bats?
>> Yeah.
>> What?
>> Bats.
>> I didn't know what was going
on.
There was a bowl of bat in the
middle of our table.
And James, of course, James,
reaches in and grabs a bat and
throws it on his plate and just
starts chowing down on this bat.
I guess it's a Micronesian
thing.
I don't know.
>> Oh, James, it's, like wet.
You have, like, wet bat in your
hand right now.
>> I mean, how often do you get
a chance to eat a bat?
It's one of the things you have
to try, and it was good.
It was like a juicy rabbit.
So, I mean, I'm going to
probably eat another one.
>> I was thinking of a tribe
name.
Like, the name for good here is
Dabu.
So we can do Dabu.
>> Dabu.
I like Dabu.
>> Okay.
>> Cheers!
>> Our new tribe.
>> Good times.
With Gabu?
Or Dabu?
>> An experience that we're
never going to forget.
>> I told everybody Dabu means
good in Micronesian, but really
I pretty much just made it up.
I love that everyone thinks,
like, "Oh, Erik looked up
Micronesian."
Hell, no, I didn't look up
Micronesian.
I just wanted to name the tribe
something funny.
For all I care it could have
been "Momo," or, like,
"Fosshizzle," or something.
I don't know.
I like Dabu.
>> I like Dabu, too.
>> Does everyone want to agree
that, like, let's enjoy this,
and then, you know, then we're
back to the game?
But take time, just, "Boom."
>> Talk, get to know each other.
>> I would like that.
>> When you merge two tribes,
all of a sudden, it becomes a
much more interpersonal game.
Your alliances become very
fuzzy, because at this point
it's ten individual people that
you now have to survive another
17 days with, and it kind of
becomes more who do you get
along with.
>> I flipped out.
I was like, "Oh, my god."
I was so happy.
>> It was basically my doing.
I'm ready to go beyond fans
versus favorites.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm ready to look past that
whole thing and really
understand that... that, yeah.
I mean, I like you a lot.
>> You know, I had a great time
with Ozzy out on Exile, and I am
a fan, you know.
So I was just kind of excited to
come out here and get to know
him.
And I felt like it was very
genuine from both sides.
>> I think that you really do
deserve to be here, and I would
rather have you here than
somebody else.
>> Yeah, right.
>> I know Alexis likes Ozzy, but
me and Ozzy have been doing this
together for 22 days now, and
she just comes in and makes
herself all comfortable, and,
yeah, it bothers me a little
bit.
I want her gone.
>> Wow!
>> What are you up to?
>> Whatever.
>> Good to be back.
>> Good to be here.
>> Oh, my god.
The Malakal beach.
Heaven.
>> Wow.
>> Look how scenic this is.
I feel like I'm in the land of
milk and honey over here,
because they have this huge open
space where they have their day
shelter, and they have a huge
cave where, like, people can
hang out if it rains.
It's ridiculous how nice it is
here.
>> A little siesta in the shade.
>> It's going to be a little
hard getting used to seeing
these new folks just grabbing
stuff and picking.
It's like people coming into
your house and picking up the
remote and turning the channel.
I mean, granted, we're all one
happy team now, so we'll all
just have to get along.
>> Cool.
>> You guys got a spear, too?
>> Yeah, we've got two.
>> Nice.
>> Yeah.
>> Flippers?
>> Actually, I've been waiting
all game for you to teach me.
>> Flippers, too?
>> No, but, I mean, I'm a good
diver.
>> Jason is a big fan of mine,
but he probably believes that he
can do it all better, and he
probably wants to prove himself
to me or to the world.
And he's going to prove himself
or he's not.
But going to Exile, I found out
someone has taken my planted
idol.
Most likely, it's Jason.
To me, I think he's the only one
who would have had the
opportunity to look who hasn't
been voted out.
So I think that Jason walking
around with my fake hidden
immunity idol is a beautiful
thing.
I think it's poetry in the
making.
>> I brought the hidden immunity
idol with me from Airai.
So right now I'm kind of just
walking around, scoping out
areas where I think, you know, I
might hide it.
The sooner I can get it out of
my bag, the more comfortable
I'll feel.
Hopefully, you know, nobody will
discover it here.
I'm just going to try to tuck it
up in this rock here real nice,
so that, you know, nobody's
walking by... so that when
somebody is walk by, they won't
see it.
So I'm going to... you know,
hopefully I won't forget this
spot either.
>> What happened?
>> With Ami?
>> Yeah.
>> Did you ask Amanda or anyone?
>> Yeah, she said Ami was trying
to vote Ozzy out.
>> Yep.
>> Well, you know, regardless of
what happened with her, that you
guys have my loyalty 100%.
You know that, right?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, I guess she just
thought, you know, she could
save herself.
>> The old Malakal?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know.
>> I mean I don't know.
>> I know, but things have
changed, and it's, like, a whole
different game, you know?
>> Now that the two tribes have
merged, it's an individual game.
Ami's gone and I feel
outnumbered, and I feel on the
outs.
I don't feel like I have any
real close allies, except for
Jason.
I mean, if I at least got in
with the favorites, then it
would be, "Okay, I can get my
way to the final six and then
work from there."
But if I'm not even in with
them, I could be next to go.
I mean, this is just... this is
a disaster.
>> I don't know what's going on
yet, honestly.
I'm not going to lie to you.
>> Okay.
I appreciate that.
>> With the merge, it's not fans
versus favorites anymore, I
don't think.
>> I hope you'll keep me in the
loop.
>> Yeah.
>> Of course, Eliza is always
trying to scramble something
together because she's always on
the outside.
And I think it's hilarious that
she's still trying to come up to
me and tell me that she's loyal,
and 100% true to the end.
Like, how can anyone be so
ridiculous?
I have missed you so much.
>> Oh, my god.
>> You don't know how long I've
been dying to just have this
conversation with you, because
I'm like, "I just want her to
know everything that's going
on."
>> Eliza's staring at us.
She's always staring at us.
She's over there staring at us.
I can't have her here anymore.
>> I'm so sick of her.
>> She's going next.
She has to.
>> And they're like... they're
like, "Yeah, but, honestly...
"Well, me and
Amanda are really tight, and
it's pretty much unbreakable."
And they understand.
I've put us in an alliance
without you being there.
But at least the game's
revolving around us, which is
good.
But we're in such a mess because
these people are voting in the
end for who gets the million.
>> I know.
>> And if we ( bleep ) them
over...
>> Well, it's inevitable now.
Parvati pretty much screwed me
over, because I don't want to be
in an alliance with Natalie and
Alexis.
I don't want to go up against
Alexis at the end.
She's a motivational speaker,
for crying out loud.
Well, well, well.
>> Yeah, so here's our pickle,
and we're in it.
Now I might as well go make an
alliance with Erik, Jason, and
Eliza right now, a triple
pickle.
>> Might as well.
>> I mean, I giggled about it to
her, but it's not funny.
>> Everybody's on the same page
about Eliza.
>> I'm livid, and it leaves me
with a lot of questions about
Parvati.
>> Tree mail.
>> "If you feel you're in over
your head...
>> ...and you're worried about
being voted out...
>> ...the only way to guarantee
you're safe is to be the last
one to bail out."
>> Oh!
>> Endurance.
>> It's bailing water or
something.
>> Maybe it's as the tide comes
in.
>> Yeah.
>> You start to drown?
>> I'd say that Eliza and myself
are definitely still on the
outskirts of any kind of
alliances in the new Dabu tribe,
but the hidden immunity idol is
definitely my biggest bargaining
chip.
If I can win the individual
immunity challenge, it will, you
know, allow me to give away the
hidden immunity idol.
Because if I have the immunity
necklace, the votes are going to
be cast toward someone else like
Eliza.
>> ...I'd give it to you.
So think about that.
>> Okay, I'll think about it.
Jason pulls me aside and it's
like, "Oh, by the way, if I can
win the individual immunity
challenge, the hidden immunity
idol, I'll give it to you."
Who would have guessed?
I made an alliance with the
right person who was sent to
Exile one too many times.
So I'm in good spirits today.
Then whoever Jason and I vote
for, even if everyone else votes
for me, will go home.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
Alexis, you came up with a new
tribe name?
>> Yeah, Dabu is our name.
It is Micronesian for good.
And it was Erik's suggestion,
and it was awesome.
It fit perfectly.
>> JEFF: All right, you guys
ready to get it your first
individual immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: First things first.
Who's got the idol?
Tribal immunity is no more.
This is now what you covet--
individual immunity.
This now becomes the single most
important thing in this game.
Have this around your neck, you
are safe in this game.
Without it, you are most
definitely vulnerable.
Today's challenge is going to
test your ability to remain calm
when everything else in your
body urges you to do otherwise.
You're each going to take a spot
in the water underneath a grated
steel barrier.
As the tide rises, the water
will rise.
As the water rises, your
breathing space will decrease
until you have nowhere left to
breathe.
Your head must stay completely
under the grate at all times.
The person who stays in this
challenge the longest wins
immunity, is guaranteed a one in
nine shot at a million bucks.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize.
We'll get started.
>> JEFF: All right, here we go.
>> Let's rock 'n' roll.
>> JEFF: For individual
immunity.
Survivors ready?
>> Ready.
>> JEFF: Go.
This challenge is on.
( laughter )
>> Cirie, has the panic set in
yet?
>> Not quite yet.
>> Give me, like, five minutes.
Help me.
>> JEFF: Now it's going to start
to get interesting.
That water level starts to creep
up, starts covering your ears.
You can't hear anymore.
It's going to mean trouble for
people who panic.
Amanda is the first out.
Head popped up behind the grate.
You can take a spot on the
pontoon, Amanda.
What happened, Amanda?
You just weren't paying
attention?
>> No, I was, like, relaxed and
dozing, and I thought I had more
space above me than I did.
>> JEFF: The water continues to
rise.
It's starting to work its way up
your face.
Now it's getting close to the
eyes.
Your brain is going to tell you
to bail and get out of this.
Just mind over matter.
Remind yourself, you can always
take one last deep breath.
Parvati has had enough.
She opts out.
Alexis opts out right behind
Parvati.
Amanda, Parvati, and Alexis the
first three out.
Cirie has had enough.
Can't take it any longer.
Cirie is out of the challenge.
Getting very close now.
Natalie can't take it any
longer.
After lasting nearly 50 minutes,
Natalie is out of this
challenge.
We are down to five.
Eliza now completely underwater.
Eliza pops up.
Eliza is now out of the
challenge.
Erik can't take it any longer.
We are now down to three--
James, Jason, and Ozzy.
Three different strategies on
how to breathe going on.
That water is above the grate
now.
You have to have your nose and
mouth through that grate, or you
will be underwater.
Amazing.
All three of these guys still in
it.
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: This is going to be a
true test of who wants immunity
the most.
>> This is, like, painful.
>> It's painful to watch.
>> JEFF: James can't do it any
longer.
James is out.
We are now down to Jason and
Ozzy.
>> Come out, Oz.
>> JEFF: Ozzy really struggling,
but he is back up.
Ozzy comes up.
It's over.
Jason wins first individual
immunity!
>> Awww!
>> JEFF: Jason, congrats.
Come on over.
Nice work.
Individual immunity.
Safe at tribal council tonight.
For the other nine of you, not
the case.
Somebody going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
See you at tribal.
>> Thank you.
>> I know, awesome, good job.
>> Quite exciting getting to
beat Ozzy.
My, quote, like, favorite player
in the game, you know, watching
him dominate in so many
challenges, and then...
>> Beating him.
>> Yep.
>> Knowing if you weren't there,
he would have won that one.
>> Yep.
Today's immunity challenge I was
able to win.
In fact, I think I actually
dominated the whole challenge.
When I came up and saw the look
of failure on Ozzy's face, it
was pretty delightful.
So being able to dominate Ozzy
and then hopefully being able to
send him home later tonight will
be one of the highlights of the
game for me.
>> Are you kidding?
>> No.
Just... I'm always, like... feel
like I'm always out of the loop.
>> You're definitely in the
loop.
>> Eliza has been my biggest
rival, I think, since the
beginning of this game.
She's been running around trying
to get me voted out personally
since day one.
I mean, everyone on this tribe
is voting for her tonight, as
far as I know.
I wouldn't have trusted her, but
if she would have tried to work
with me on the other side, it
would have been easier.
But she was trying to get me out
the whole time, and then she
comes up to me and tries to be
loyal.
I'm like, "Too little, too late,
lady."
>> Jason.
I'm pretty sure they're voting
for me, so...
>> I've got you covered.
Don't worry.
>> So we're voting Ozzy?
>> Yes.
>> You hid it?
>> Yeah.
>> Are you going to get it?
>> Yeah!
>> Okay.
>> Don't worry, baby.
I'm trusting you.
>> I'll go get it right now.
>> Okay.
My god.
It will literally be the biggest
blindside in history.
>> I can't wait to send Ozzy's
cocky ass home tonight.
He's going to be like "What?"
>> This might make me more hated
than Fairplay.
Oh, my god!
I'm so glad you won today.
>> I could have been down there
another ten minutes.
>> What's Ozzy and Alexis
talking about?
>> I don't know.
>> All of a sudden this set
comes in and, boom, just hammers
me and brings me back on the
inside.
>> Alexis is dangerous-- very,
very, very, very dangerous.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And she needs to go.
>> I'm cool with that.
I mean...
>> First.
She needs to go now.
I don't think I know Ozzy as
well as I think I know him.
>> I keep trying to tell you,
missy, he's playing.
>> Well, I'm playing, too.
>> I know.
Amanda seems to believe that we
should probably get rid of
Alexis, and I think a small bit
of jealousy is coming into play
because of the relationship that
Ozzy has with Alexis.
Will he vote her?
>> Yeah.
I don't... I think so.
>> But as long as it's not me,
then I'll vote Alexis.
>> It's in my bag.
>> This is so stupid.
This is just a napkin.
Oh, my god.
This isn't it.
Jason, come here.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to pull?
I'm going home anyhow.
It's not the idol.
>> It is the idol.
>> It's not the idol.
>> Yes, it is.
>> Ozzy must have put it in
there.
He must have the real thing.
That's not the idol.
>> What is it?
>> It's a ( no audio ) stick.
>> I know.
It has a face on it.
Don't worry.
>> Ozzy put it in there and made
a face on it.
>> No, he didn't.
>> It's not the idol.
>> Why do you say that?
>> Because that can't be the
idol.
>> Why not?
>> Because it's just a stick.
>> I know.
Do you think so?
>> I think that that's not the
idol.
>> Then that's a bummer.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> JEFF: Alexis, one of the
things that happens when you
merge is it's the first time
everybody's together, all at
once.
Gives you the opportunity to
start assessing skills.
How much time have you spent
looking at people that are now
new to you thinking, "This is
how they're playing"?
>> I think there are three main
points that define strength in
this game.
You know, are they a stronger
social player?
Are they a stronger physical
player?
Are they a stronger mental
So I think the merge is the
first opportunity where you
really get to see your entire
competition versus the
competition within your own
tribe.
>> JEFF: Cirie, Alexis brings up
three different types of skills.
What skills do you see that
Alexis has?
>> So far, I'd say Alexis has
all three.
Socially around camp, physically
during the challenges, and she's
mentally strong.
So I think she's, like, a triple
threat.
Sorry.
>> JEFF: Alexis, is that a
little worrisome to be outed as
a triple threat?
>> I don't think at this point
in the game.
I mean, there's ten people left
out of 20, so I think there are
several people here left who
maintain a triple threat.
I don't think you make it this
far if you're not mentally,
physically, socially
competitive.
>> JEFF: You talk about your
skill list.
Tell me about Eliza's skills.
>> I think that Eliza played an
incredible physical and mental
game.
I don't think she played as well
a social game.
>> JEFF: You say "Played."
>> Pardon me?
>> You said it in past tense, as
if I've already been voted out.
>> Okay, I'm sorry.
>> It's okay.
>> JEFF: Eliza, do you agree
with that?
Are you strong and weak as she
says?
>> Alexis' assessment was
probably right on.
I think that my social game
potentially has been lacking.
But I think that a lot of people
here are playing a very short-
sighted game, and not really
looking down the line.
So they're overestimating their
own social game, I think.
>> JEFF: So, Ozzy, there's two
sides of this social skill.
There's the side that's
threatening because the person
is very good socially.
The other side is the person is
so bad socially that maybe you
keep them around.
>> Yeah, you take someone who
nobody likes to the end, and you
win.
>> That's the way to
win Survivor.
There's no book to win
Survivor.
That's the schedule.
Get the one that everybody hates
and keep them along, yeah.
>> JEFF: Eliza, you can't miss
your eyes when they roll.
Do you think you're liked?
>> No, not really.
>> She's liked.
>> No, I'm not really liked.
>> Well, Eliza, you've been
running around back and forth
trying to vote me out since day
one, then coming back to me
yesterday telling me you're
going to be 100% loyal to me,
that we need to stay true to the
old Malakal tribe and favorites
to the end.
Are you kidding me?
People are going to believe you?
>> That's not true.
Everyone is saying we would
stick together, we would stick
together.
>> But what were you trying to
do to me the first day?
What were you trying to do to
me?
>> I was not trying to do
anything to you.
>> I just can't sit here and be
quiet anymore, because it's...
it's just too much for me.
>> JEFF: Eliza, welcome to
tribal council.
No free rides.
>> I mean, I definitely got
myself into this mess.
But everyone is here to win a
million dollars.
I mean, you know, people have
come awfully close and lost
because they went up against the
best.
You know, so it's, like, are you
really going to make the same
mistake again?
I mean, bring people people
don't like to the finals with
you, and have a shot, plain and
simple.
>> JEFF: All right, it is time
to get to the vote.
Jason, you have the individual
immunity necklace.
If at any time you want to
assign it to someone else,
whether at the beach or here at
tribal council, you can do that.
>> You know, I feel like I have
no alliances at the new Dabu
tribe.
I don't think anyone had a
conversation with me the entire
afternoon.
>> JEFF: So Jason is clearly not
going to give up the necklace.
You cannot vote for Jason.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
>> I hope something miraculous
happens with the stick and
you're voted out, not me.
>> It was your bad luck to pick
the wrong girl to mess with.
Hope you learn from your
mistakes the second time around.
>> Tonight my vote is for Ozzy.
Hopefully what I gave Eliza is
the real hidden immunity idol.
I can't wait to see the look on
your face if it is you.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
The rules of Survivor state that
if a hidden immunity idol is
played, then any votes cast
against that person do not
count, and the person with the
next highest number of votes
would be voted out.
This is not a hidden immunity
idol.
>> That means Ozzy has it.
Jason found it on Exile.
Ozzy has the real one.
>> Sorry, I couldn't tell you
guys, but...
>> But it was worth a shot.
>> Jeff, come on.
That took hours to make.
>> JEFF: Okay, once the votes
are read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Eliza.
Ozzy.
One vote Eliza, one vote Ozzy.
Two votes Ozzy, one vote Eliza.
Eliza.
We're tied, two votes Eliza, two
votes Ozzy.
Eliza.
That's three votes Eliza, two
votes Ozzy.
Eliza.
Four votes Eliza.
That's five votes Eliza, two
votes Ozzy.
Ninth person voted out, and the
first member of our jury, Eliza.
That's six.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Eliza, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> JEFF: Well, it would seem
this fans versus favorite
competition might indeed be
over, and we're left with a
group of nine individuals, all
with an equal shot at winning
this game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
The winning team will fly to one
of the federated states of
Micronesia.
Yeah.
Ozzy with a big lead!
>> This game is outwit,
outplay...
>> Outlast, yeah.
>> Well, I think I did
everything I could do in this
game.
I think I went out with a bang,
played a fake hidden immunity
idol.
I can't really believe that
Jason thought that stick was the
real hidden immunity idol, but I
had to play it anyhow, out Ozzy
for having the real one, and
hopefully now people can do
something about it.
Too bad that immunity idol
wasn't real, because we would
have shocked them.