>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Ozzy found the hidden immunity
idol on Exile Island and
replaced it with a fake one as a
decoy.
The idol put Ozzy and his
alliance of Amanda, Parvati, and
James in control of the game.
>> It's in our little four
clique, and I think it's going
to stay in our little four
clique.
>> JEFF: But their control was
short-lived....
Drop your buffs.
We are switching tribes.
...as the fans and favorites
were mixed.
You must choose somebody from
the opposite tribe.
>> James.
>> JEFF: James joins the new
Airai tribe.
Ozzy's alliance was split when
James and Parvati went to Airai.
>> Oh, don't look so pissed off.
The new Malakal tribe combined
Ozzy, Amanda, Amy, and Cirie
from the favorites with Joel,
Erik, Tracy, and Chet from the
fans.
The new Airai combined James,
Parvati, Jonathan, and Eliza
from the favorites with Natalie,
Alexis, Jason, and Kathy from
the fans.
At the new Airai...
>> Ow!
Damn it!
>> JEFF: Jonathan was seriously
injured and required stitches.
But his injury didn't keep his
tribe from winning immunity.
Airai wins!
At Malakal, Joel came up with a
plan.
>> What do you think?
>> JEFF: But the favorites had a
different idea.
>> Joel is a bigger threat for
us than Chet is.
>> JEFF: At tribal council, the
fans on the new Malakal tribe
got a firsthand lesson on how
the favorites operate.
The favorites used Tracy and
Chet to blindside Joel.
Joel, the tribe has spoken.
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Joel just kind of sat there
just in disbelief, and then at
the end of it, he didn't, like,
make any emotion at all.
And then he was gone.
I felt pretty shafted to see
Joel go.
I mean, those guys are tough as
nails.
You cannot trust favorites at
all.
They're tanks.
I mean, they have armor on.
If the playing field has been
lowered to lying and just
tricking people straight to
their face, I think I might have
to do some of that.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Cirie, come play with us!
>> I'll be right there.
>> Whatever.
>> We had no other choice.
Joel was popping anyway.
It was so hard to vote off Joel.
They had four and we had four.
And we should have gained
control against the favorites.
But Joel was hell bent on
getting rid of Chet, taking away
my alliance.
So what are you going to do?
And this is absolutely driving
me batty not being in control.
>> ...to bend over.
>> These guys are vicious.
>> They are so vicious.
And I think you are next to go.
You're a threat.
They don't want to compete
against you.
>> Yeah, they aren't going to
take you with them.
You need to understand that.
They're not going to take me
with them.
The only thing that we can do is
to try to get one of them to
vote with us.
If we can get one of them off,
then we're back.
That's all we need.
I'm just going to boil a bunch
to get it really soft.
>> You look like a chicken
farmer.
>> Are you doing okay?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Right where you are right now
is where I was when I first came
here.
>> Tracy seemed like she'd given
up, so I went and had a pep talk
with her.
Even though I'm, like, at the
bottom of the rung in the old
Malakal, I'm not going to be poo
pants, because the more you're
poo pants, the sooner you're
going out.
You've just got to keep on
going, you know?
>> Thanks.
>> Yeah, of course.
I just don't like to see when
somebody is having a really
rough time.
And I know how it feels.
>> I was never part of the
original alliance between James,
Parvati, Cirie, Amanda, and
Ozzy.
So I'm also in a very vulnerable
situation.
Maybe I need to play the game a
little differently, but I'm
thinking in baby steps right
now, and we'll see what happens.
>> It's feeling better.
More slowly than I wish, but it
is getting there.
No question.
But it would just suck, because
he's really a good motivator, a
good guy to have around.
>> I loved it.
I think we turned out... I mean,
we got the wrong beach, we got
the better tribe, for sure.
>> Fans versus favorites is over
in my mind.
As a new Airai tribe, we are
four fans and four favorites,
but I think once we earn the
fans' trust, Jonathan and I are
going to try to work with them,
and definitely get rid of
Parvati and James before there
is any type of merge and they
can get back with Amanda and
Ozzy.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
Malakal, come on in.
Airai getting your first look at
the new Malakal tribe.
>> Joel is out?
>> JEFF: Joel voted out at the
last tribal council.
>> JEFF: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: On my go, both tribes
will swim out and collect
several bundles of planks,
sticks, and rope.
You'll have ten minutes to use
these materials to build a
blockade in the other tribe's
tunnel.
Once the ten minutes are up,
you'll then race to tear down
the blockade that the other
tribe built in your tunnel.
First tribe to get all their
members through their tunnel and
on the mat win reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: For the winning tribe,
two native Micronesians who
spent their entire life living
off this land will come to your
camp and show you how to get the
most out of it.
If you pay attention, it will
change camp life.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Absolutely!
>> JEFF: In addition, the
winning tribe will choose one
member from the losing tribe to
go to Exile Island.
You will also select one member
from your own tribe to join
them.
On Exile, you'll find a clue to
the whereabouts of the hidden
immunity idol.
Airai, you have one extra
member.
Sitting somebody out.
Cannot sit out the same person
in back-to-back challenges.
Who's it going to be?
>> I think I can be very helpful
in putting this together and
pushing through.
Absolutely.
>> I'll sit out.
>> JEFF: Natalie is going to sit
this one out.
Take a spot on the bench, give
you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You've got to swim out, collect
all your materials, get them
back to your mat before you can
start building.
Ozzy first to the platform for
Malakal.
Jason right behind for Airai.
Jason tossing them out to his
tribemates.
Ozzy and Erik tossing them out
to their tribemates.
>> All right, bring them back!
Start moving them back!
>> JEFF: Ozzy and Erik making
their way back.
James and Kathy heading back
with a couple of bundles for
Airai.
Ami right behind with bundles
for Malakal.
Penner really limping on that
bad leg.
Trying to muscle them up.
Penner takes a big fall.
That leg is really giving him
trouble.
Malakal, you have everything.
Start building!
Airai has everything back.
They're building.
You have ten minutes to use all
these materials to build a
blockade in the other tribe's
tunnel.
You're trying to prevent them
from getting through.
>> JEFF: Cirie, Ozzy, and Tracy
have got a blockade going in the
front.
>> JAMIE: A lot of quiet tribe
strategy going on.
You have five minutes left.
Last 30 seconds.
Make them count.
Big reward.
When the time is up, I'm going
to tell to you switch sides, and
you will start tearing down what
the other tribe has built up.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Switch.
Now your goal is to get through
the blockade the other tribe
just created.
Malakal making quick work of
Airai's first big blockade.
The Airai tribe having a little
more trouble.
>> Let's push it out, Oz.
>> JAMIE: Ozzy is in the tunnel
for Malakal.
Malakal already making their way
through their tunnel.
Airai not even in theirs yet.
Penner, bad leg and all, ripping
those planks out of there.
>> JEFF: Cirie and Ozzy are in
the tunnel for Malakal.
Jason the first to go in for
Airai.
Crawling over the top.
He's halfway through.
Eliza right behind.
Got to get all tribe members
through the tunnel and onto the
mat.
Doesn't matter if you leave any
of the blockade behind.
Just get yourselves through.
>> Come on, get through.
>> Push through, guys, push
through.
Looking good, guys!
Looking good!
>> Go!
Go!
>> JEFF: Airai has a lot of
members getting through this
tunnel quickly, all of a sudden.
They got through the first big
blockade and that's all there
was.
Eliza is out, Parvati is out.
Malakal falling behind now.
Alexis is through.
James and Jason staying inside
to help people through.
Penner dragging himself through.
>> JEFF: Airai almost through
their tunnel.
Ozzy trying to get out.
Kathy's through.
Ozzy is out for Malakal.
Penner's through.
Airai wins reward!
Airai, congratulations.
First order of business, choose
one member of the Malakal tribe
to go to Exile Island.
Who is it going to be?
>> Chet.
>> JEFF: Chet.
All right, now, Airai, you have
to choose somebody to join Chet,
someone from your own tribe.
Who's going to go?
>> Good man.
>> JEFF: Jason going to Exile
Island along with Chet.
You guys will rejoin your tribes
at the next immunity challenge.
Malakal, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Good job, guys.
>> Bye.
>> JEFF: All right, Airai,
here's what's going to happen--
you're going to go back to your
camp.
Two native Micronesians are
going to show up.
Utilize these guys.
Ask them every question you can
think of.
Before that happens, Penner,
medical's going to take a look
at that knee.
>> Do you have any pain in your
groin at all, up in here?
Is it a bit tender in here?
>> Yeah, a little bit, but not
terrible.
>> See, I mean, Jonathan,
there's a big abscess in there,
a big collection of pus.
This is going to need
intravenous antibiotics.
It probably needs surgical
washout.
It's not going to be a quick
fix.
>> Oh, god bless it.
I'm not quitting.
>> I can only recommend that you
get treatment in hospital for
the sake of your knee.
Antibiotics are not working at
this stage.
It's showing signs of spreading
around your body.
It's moved up into your lymph
nodes.
It can make you really, really
sick, okay?
An infection that goes into your
bloodstream is potentially
fatal.
>> Oh, god!
Okay.
>> JEFF: So this isn't a case of
"Another afternoon, I'll come
check you later in today"?
>> I can only recommend for the
sake of his leg and his life
that he leave the game now.
He needs hospital treatment.
It's not going to get better.
It will just get worse.
>> JEFF: What can you do?
>> I know.
Sorry, guys.
Bad luck on Johnny.
I had this game, too.
I saw the daylight.
>> JEFF: All right, let's let
you say good-bye to your tribe.
We'll get you on a boat and get
you fixed up.
>> I'm sorry, guys.
>> It's okay.
>> We're sorry.
>> I couldn't have done
everything else.
They did everything they could
do.
And they've got to take me to
the hospital right now.
I loved hanging out with all you
guys.
>> We'll miss you.
>> All right, baby.
Take care.
>> Jonathan, you take care of
yourself.
>> We need you.
We need you.
I need you.
>> I'm sorry.
>> I really hate to see him go.
He was like the pillar of
strength around camp, and, so,
yeah, it's... I'm sad to see him
go.
I only knew him for, like, three
days, but what I knew, I loved
him, you know?
>> I'm proud of you guys.
>> You just kicked ass at that
last challenge.
>> Have fun, guys.
I'll see you at the reunion.
>> All right.
>> JEFF: Want me to give you a
hand?
>> I've got it, Jeff.
Thank you.
>> JEFF: Take it on your own.
Hey, hate to see you go, man.
Pleasure.
>> Pleasure was mine, buddy.
It really was.
I'll see you later.
I was kicking ass in this game.
I swear to god.
I don't want to be out of the
game.
But I don't want to lose my leg.
Couldn't have tried any better.
Couldn't have fought any harder.
It was fun while it lasted.
>> Poor Jonathan.
>> I needed Jonathan, because
these girls are driving me
crazy.
I'm with a bunch of girls, and
I'm not that persuasive in
the verbal manner to woo people
on my side, and they are.
>> Two guys.
>> If I make it to the merge
it's all good, but chances of me
making it are not that... this
is not in my favor right now.
>> Yay!
Hi!
>> Hi!
>> Welcome.
>> Hi.
>> When Edwin and Joe came, they
brought a fishing line.
They brought an extra machete, a
knife, a paring knife.
>> Yes, I am.
>> That's okay.
( laughs )
We can still hang out.
>> They brought a fishing net we
can cast out to catch bait.
They brought vegetables,
fruits-- I mean, just amazing,
amazing stuff.
We were thrilled.
>> The first thing we'll do, I'm
going to set up the bait for the
crab.
We'll show you how to do it.
>> Yeah, great.
>> And then after that, we're
going to show you how to fish.
>> I got one.
>> Yay!
>> I think this is one of the
best rewards we've gotten,
because we can actually
continually use this knowledge
and come out here and fish in
the morning instead of eating
just coconuts day after day
after day.
It's going to be amazing for us.
>> Yeah!
>> Attagirl!
>> They're, like, slowing us
down.
I felt like the challenge today
was us four against the whole
tribe over there.
>> Yeah.
>> Did you feel like that?
>> ...and I lost, I couldn't go
back to my job.
( laughter )
>> Yeah.
We lost the reward challenge
today.
It's our third challenge in a
row that we lost as the new
Malakal tribe.
We just don't work well as a
team.
And we need the fans to step it
up.
>> She's like, what, 53?
At least 55.
It's just... you know what's
getting on my nerves?
That not only do you have to
play the game, you have to teach
them the game, too.
I don't want to teach.
>> It's starting to kind of get
to me, the fan bashing.
Yeah, they seem slow and they're
not doing anything, but you know
what?
They're coming around.
And we were there once, too.
So I'm kind of starting to feel,
you know what?
Why not give them a chance?
>> I thought about your
position, and if we can stick
together and help each other
out, then...
>> How tight are you and Cirie,
pretty tight?
>> No.
>> When you guys first came to
camp, I was happy to vote for
Cirie then.
>> I know Erik wants to vote for
her.
>> Really?
>> Who else would vote for her?
>> Chet, me, Erik, and you, and
then she'd be gone.
And I'd feel better.
It's just that she's got such a
cute smile and you want to trust
her.
>> She's really sweet, but
there's that side that's like...
see, that's exactly why I came
and talked to you guys.
I had the same uneasy feeling.
I'm really conflicted right now.
The thing is, I just don't trust
Cirie, I just don't.
She screwed me over once when
she voted out Yau-Man.
And I feel it coming again.
>> I hope so.
>> I really trust you.
>> You should.
>> I really, really trust you.
>> Look, I'll look you right...
I trust you.
>> I trust you, too.
>> Okay?
>> Okay.
Do you feel so much better?
>> Oh, my gosh, yes.
>> Like a new person.
>> Like a whole new person.
I'm giving all my trust to you.
>> Okay.
>> Take care of me.
Take care of me, you guys,
please, because I'm really
sticking my neck out there, you
guys.
>> I wonder if Jason found the
idol.
Chet probably got under that
little cave and just stayed
there.
>> I have the real immunity
idol, and after I found the
immunity idol, I decided to
fashion a fake one of my own,
and I wrapped it back up and hid
it right back where I found it.
I really want Jason to find the
fake one, because, from what
I've heard, he might be naive
enough to believe that it's the
real one and use it in some
manner that might end up getting
him voted off.
>> We can just do what we need
to do for us.
>> Yeah, take your time.
I'm just going to go, like, get
a little organized, and then
maybe go search or something.
>> Okay.
That's fine.
>> The other day, in one of the
challenges, I got a piece of
coral sort of wedged up into my
foot, and it really hurts, like,
really bad and it's sort of like
an infection.
So I feel like I'm at the end of
my tether right now, and I don't
it to get any worse or anything.
I mean, obviously my health is
more important right now.
>> "Clue number one.
To progress further go back to
the start.
The thing which you covet
requires ascension."
Chet believes Ozzy holds the
hidden immunity idol already, so
I think he's given up on the
hope of finding it.
Me, on the other hand, you know,
I'm going to keep looking and
see what happens.
"Continue your quest by crossing
the ocean.
You've done it before, now
repeat the motion."
Back over.
"Two legs rising out of the sea.
Over your head but under a
rock."
Put on your shoes and go for a
walk."
Well, I guess this is the hidden
immunity idol.
It's not much, but it's a
carving of a piece of wood with
a little guy on it.
And...
this is pretty incredible.
So, you know, I'm going to have
to hold on to this tight.
This means Ozzy doesn't have it.
I have it, so this is really
good for me.
Sweet!
>> See that?
See that?
Come here.
Right here.
It's eating now, it's eating.
Right there, see?
See that?
>> Yeah.
Come here.
>> So where's your plate?
>> Right here.
My god.
It's so good.
>> I love garlic, anything in
garlic.
>> Oh, the fish stew is hands
down the best meal we've had so
far.
It was delicious.
I think we had 25 different
types of fish tonight, on top of
all the incredible seasonings
that they brought with them, and
just kind of showing us how to
do it.
>> Oh, it smells good!
>> Oh!
>> Oh, boy!
( speaking a Micronesian
language )
>> Bottoms up.
>> Bottoms up!
>> Woo!
>> JEFF: Malakal, come on in.
Airai, come on in.
>> He's not on there?
>> Where's Jonathan?
>> He got evacuated.
>> He got evacuated?
>> Oh, my god!
>> Holy crapola.
>> JEFF: We'll now bring in Chet
and Jason returning from Exile
Island.
>> Yay!
>> How you doing, Chet?
>> Tough days.
>> Jason, we lost Jonathan.
>> Because of his leg?
>> He had to go.
>> JEFF: All right, let me catch
everybody up.
Jonathan Penner is, obviously,
not here.
I think everybody here knows
that at a previous challenge, he
got injured.
The doctors came in to check his
stitches.
They saw that an infection had
started.
They assessed it and made the
decision that it was too risky
to let him stay in the game,
because if the infection spread,
it would become life-
threatening.
They took him to the hospital,
performed surgery, opened up the
wound, cleaned it out.
He's doing fine.
So we're now even, seven-seven,
again.
Game continues.
Switching topics.
Chet, Jason, did you guys have
any time to look for the idol
out on Exile?
>> Well, yeah, it was a long
time out there.
But I kind of gave up.
And the conclusion I've come to
right now is that Ozzy has
already discovered the hidden
immunity idol.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, interesting play
going on.
Only a few people have been to
Exile, so only a few of you
really know the truth about
what's happening out there.
>> I don't know if he isn't that
good at following clues, or if
someone else has found it.
I guess we're only going to find
out in the next couple of days.
>> JEFF: All right.
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yep.
>> JEFF: For today's challenge,
both tribes will use stepping
poles to transfer two tribe
members from one large platform
to another.
All seven tribe members must
then swim out to a final very
small tower.
First tribe to get all seven
tribe members to the top of the
tower with both feet on or above
the top deck wins immunity, safe
from tribal council.
Losers, date with me.
Somebody going home.
We are even at seven-seven.
Nobody sitting it out.
I'll give you a chance to
strategize.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's a big collision as you've
got to switch lanes to begin.
First step, untie the stepping
poles.
Tracy and Ami going to be
carried across the water for
Malakal.
Eliza and Parvati for Airai.
Takes a lot of teamwork in this
challenge.
>> Okay, I'm on.
>> Way to go, guys.
Slow and steady.
>> JEFF: Wow, Airai trying to
outthink the challenge, not
using two poles.
>> Way to go.
>> JEFF: James carrying the
pole.
The rest of the tribe keeping it
steady.
If it works, it is a great
strategy.
And it does.
Eliza is across.
Great idea, great execution by
Airai.
Not the way this challenge was
designed or the way we thought
it would go.
Airai going to try it again with
Parvati.
Can she keep her balance?
Malakal sticking with their plan
of using both poles.
They have not stolen Airai's
strategy.
James is powering Airai to a
huge lead.
Airai has-- oh!
Oh!
It almost worked.
>> Wait, she didn't touch...
>> No, you're down.
You're using the ladder.
All the way to the back.
Airai was very close.
Parvati fell off at the last
second.
Got to go all the way back to
the start.
Airai giving it another go.
Parvati trying to balance again.
Malakal taking a lot of time,
making very little progress.
Airai very close again.
Will it work?
Parvati's across.
Eliza's across.
Everybody to the platform.
Malakal still working on their
first tribe member as Airai
climbs up the final tower.
You've got to get all seven
people on or above the top deck.
>> Help me, help me, somebody.
>> JEFF: Cirie is losing it.
Tracy very close.
Can she get there from there?
She is.
Malakal has the first tribe
member across.
They're heading back to pick up
Ami.
Everyone in Airai hanging on to
James, trying to figure out how
to get seven people on a
platform built for five.
Immunity at stake.
Malakal now using Airai's
strategy.
Are they too late?
>> Okay, my foot's up.
>> One, two, three.
>> Jeff!
>> JEFF: Airai has it!
Airai wins immunity!
Airai, creative thinking made
that a very easy win for you
guys.
Come on over and get immunity.
Congratulations.
No tribal council for Airai.
Safe in this game at least one
more day.
Malakal, tribal council tonight.
One of you going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
it out.
I'll see you at tribal.
Get in your boat and head back.
>> Well, if he had to have
immediate surgery, it's pretty
bad.
>> I expected him to go out in,
like, a ball of blazing...
>> Blazing glory.
>> Yeah.
>> How are you feeling?
>> A fish hook?
Why?
>> I need to do some surgery on
my foot.
>> No!
>> Look at this.
Isn't this, like, a pocket of
just pus?
>> I would not open that out
here.
>> That's what's hurt.
That's what it is.
I just want to open it up and
get that out and the pain will
be gone.
>> Don't do that.
>> You ready to go, huh?
>> Oh, man.
Damn.
Losing everyone.
What is going on, man?
We lost the immunity challenge
yet again.
And all of a sudden, Chet comes
up and says, "Please do me a
favor and vote me out tonight."
I was like, "All right, Chet,
we'll vote you out."
Was there any question anyways?
>> Dropping like flies.
>> Took the words out of my
mouth.
>> Craziness.
>> Everything frickin' changes
on a dime in this game.
>> Chet's injured, he's done.
He wants to leave the game by
being voted out, because he
thinks that's honorable.
But I think it would be totally
more honorable to help Tracy,
his longtime friend since he's
been in this game, and myself to
get out, like, one of the bigger
threats right now.
We need him so bad just so we
can get Cirie out right now or
Ozzy, even.
>> What if Ozzy's got the idol?
>> If Chet makes it all the way
until tribal and votes, it would
be amazing.
>> Chet and I are tight.
And I understand he's sick, but
it is imperative that Chet vote
with us today.
If he doesn't, I'm screwed.
But I'm not going to put his
name down.
I won't do it.
>> You're just more than ready,
huh?
>> Come on, guys.
I have too much going on right
now.
And these last two days have
been total hell.
I can't even think straight.
Please, that's all I'm asking.
>> You could help take Ozzy
down, because he's not expecting
it.
This would be the craziest play
ever in the history of this game
if you helped us do this.
>> The target keeps changing.
Now Erik and Tracy are looking
at Ozzy, going, "Ozzy might have
the idol, he's a threat."
And I'm definitely going to have
to deal with Ozzy at some point.
So if Tracey and Erik convince
Chet to stay in the game and
make a vote, I would vote with
them.
>> I know.
>> If you did this for us, it
would be the biggest gift you
could give us on the way out to
just take a little pride.
Me and Tracy would be so
grateful.
We would be amazingly grateful
for that, that you could use
your last dying breath to do
something for us in this game.
I would be incredibly grateful.
>> Just think about it, okay?
>> I'll think about it.
Tracy and I committed to each
other from day one that we would
do whatever we could for each
other, but I've been having some
issues with my foot and some
other health issues.
I pretty much told them I would
take the hit tonight.
But Tracy and Erik have another
plan up their sleeve.
They want to use my vote to try
to take out Ozzy.
I did tell Tracy and Erik I
would think about it, and I will
think about it, but to be
honest, I'm not sure what I'm
going to do.
>> JEFF: Cirie, was there much
discussion today about Penner's
exit in regards to how difficult
this game really is?
>> It just sucks to go out the
way he did.
I know if he could have argued
the point, he would still be
here.
>> JEFF: He tried.
>> I'm sure he did.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, when you see
somebody go out like that, what
goes through your head?
>> Jonathan is the last
person... I thought he was just
a really strong guy.
And I've seen him get cut worse,
and you don't think a that
little bug gets in you, and,
boom, you're all of a sudden
out of the game.
>> JEFF: Erik, at today's
challenge, Jason made a comment
after going to Exile, basically
saying, "I've been there.
I looked around.
I think Ozzy has the idol."
Did that put any thoughts in
your head?
>> What Jason said definitely
put some thoughts in my head.
And I wouldn't put it past Ozzy
that he found the idol.
That's based on knowing Ozzy.
>> JEFF: Cirie, when you hear
Jason's comment, do you, like
Erik, believe him at face value?
>> No, I don't really take
anything anybody out here says
at face value.
Jason could have it himself and
is trying to throw us off his
track by saying Ozzy had it.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, does that concern
you?
>> I'm not the one going home
tonight.
I mean, everybody knows who's
going home, so it's not really
of any concern.
I mean, if I do get voted off
tonight, I will be so blown away
and so blindsided that I'll just
get naked and jump off the pier
right now.
I mean, let's be honest with
each other right now-- Chet's
going home tonight.
And if somehow everyone is not
voting that way, then I have no
business being here.
>> JEFF: You wouldn't be the
first to be blindsided.
>> That's true, that's very
true.
>> JEFF: Chet?
>> Well, the way it's been in
every tribal council, there
always seems to be an obvious
person but it never turns out to
be that person.
So I think there's always going
to be that uncertainty, and that
mix of you never know exactly
what's going to happen.
>> JEFF: So Amanda, coming to
tribal council, you have an idea
who you're going to vote for.
You may have an idea who a lot
of people are going to vote for.
From a strategy point of view,
do you think twice about
everything you hear?
>> Well I've learned you're
pretty much going to be the one
gone if you start feeling
comfortable.
So I never feel comfortable.
And even though I'm pretty
certain on what's going on
tonight, you can never be
certain in this game.
>> JEFF: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Cirie, you're up.
>> Thanks for letting us use you
to vote out Joel, and I hope
your foot gets better.
>> I'm sorry to see you go.
Bye.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Chet.
Chet.
Two votes Chet.
That's three votes Chet.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Fans Versus
Favorites, Chet.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Chet, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Love you guys.
>> JEFF: Well, the good news is
you've lasted 17 days.
The bad news is you're down to
six.
Got to start winning.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
The fans at Malakal struggle to
stay in the game.
>> I'm going to fight like hell
to win immunity.
>> JEFF: While the Airai tribe
struggles to stay alive.
>> It's just savagery.
It's like you're cavemen.
>> JEFF: And Kathy's hanging on
by a thread.
>> It's brutally torturous.
>> I decided at the end not to
go with Tracy and Erik's plan to
blindside Ozzy.
I just felt that's something
they can take care of after I'm
gone.
I'm very proud of the way I
played the game.
I may be going out now, but I
lasted a lot longer than some
other people thought I would.
I am so honored to be part of
the Survivor family forever, and
it has been a great experience,
and thank you again.