>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Drop your buffs, we are
switching tribes.
The fans and favorites were
mixed, putting an even number of
fans and favorites on both
sides.
>> Oh, don't look so pissed off.
>> JEFF: After the switch, it
became obvious how much the fans
suffered.
>> I'm amazed they're still
alive, poor things.
They should be dead.
>> JEFF: And how much the
favorites thrived.
>> Those guys are tough as
nails.
>> JEFF: The new Airai gelled
immediately...
Airai wins!
...and went on a winning streak.
But they lost Jonathan due it an
injury.
>> I couldn't have done anything
else.
They did everything they could
do.
>> JEFF: On Exile Island, Ozzy
found the hidden immunity idol
and replaced it with a fake one
as a decoy, which was discovered
by Jason.
>> I guess this is the hidden
immunity idol.
>> Help me, help me, somebody.
>> JEFF: Cirie is losing it.
>> Help me, help me!
>> JEFF: Airai has it!
When the new Malakal lost their
third challenge in a row, Chet
volunteered to be voted out.
And at tribal council Erik
received two throwaway votes...
>> I vowed never to vote for
Chet.
>> JEFF: ...and Chet got the
rest...
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor: Fans Versus
Favorites, Chet.
...leaving two fans, Tracy and
Erik, on Ozzy's tribe.
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> A lot of crab.
>> Wow.
>> I think we should have the
damn thing cut open right now.
It's only laying two eggs
anyway.
>> Well, let's kill them right
now, all three of them.
Oh, the chicken issue.
Come on, girls.
I think Tracy started it for
some reason.
I'm going to blame it on Tracy.
We've got three chickens that
lay three eggs almost every
single day.
Hey, it's a renewable resource.
You want to take out a renewable
resource?
That makes no sense.
>> Like, you're not going to
kill them as soon as some more
people get off so you can have
more meat for yourself?
>> No.
No.
Not going to happen.
>> Yeah.
>> It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter the way this
game works.
>> It's three weeks, three
chickens.
>> Tracy is breeding a lot of
insecurity around camp.
Of course, she's trying to play
the game.
She's trying to scramble to save
her own ass, but we don't need
that.
Look at this-- crabs.
We've got massive crabs.
There's plenty of other food.
We just have to, like, get it.
>> Ozzy is in control of this
tribe.
He's like the kingpin.
He tells you what you can and
can't do.
He tells you when you're going
to eat.
He cooks the food and then we
have to wait until Ozzy says eat
it.
It's crazy.
I mean, it's just crazy.
Ozzy is going to win this thing
if we don't get him out of this
game.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> We're definitely on a rain
streak.
I just want to get clean.
Oh, yeah.
Another day in the lap of
luxury.
How do we do it, ladies?
>> They complain about the rain.
But they didn't get wet because
we were in the cave.
I mean, you could be like it was
before-- outside, under a bush,
getting pummeled by this rain.
>> I bet nothing can capture the
true essence of the stench
and this funk.
>> And how filthy we are right
now.
>> Deal with the funk.
It couldn't have smelled any
better than what they were in
before.
Just relax.
We're not going to be here
forever.
This is a game called
called Survivor.
>> I don't even see where
there's...
>> A sign of hope?
>> No.
>> Is my face just dirty?
>> This is just the stupidest
thing I ever did in my life.
Probably because I'm just... I'm
crabby.
I'm not a morning person.
>> Oh, baby.
>> The moods out here are you're
on one day and feeling good, and
the next day it's just all crap.
Today, this morning is a crap
day.
>> Could we just get a day of
sunshine, please?
Wash and dry our clothes.
>> Oh, my god.
Thinking of home and my washer
and dryer and my food and my
daughter and my husband, and...
Well, it's going to make me cry.
It's going to make me want to be
there.
Nope, still here.
Damn!
>> Ozzy is amazing.
I honestly like Ozzy.
He's an awesome guy, and I want
to learn.
I want to grow.
I want to go outside the small
scope that I've lived in and
just see a lot more of the
world.
And everybody thinks Ozzy is,
look, the wonderkid, or
whatever.
And I'm just like, "I can do
that.
I can climb a coconut tree,
too."
>> Some of them look like
they're stable, but then you'll
pull it, and they'll just pull
right off.
When you grab the green palm
frond, give it a little test.
>> Erik and Ozzy are like The
Lion King, the father, when he
was teaching the cub.
And you can just see, like,
stars.
Whenever he says Ozzy's name,
like, stardust comes out of his
mouth.
Erik just is like, "Ozzy..."
>> A couple of more steps and
you're there.
>> Wow.
>> Cool, huh?
Good job, dude.
>> They're bonding right now.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Yes!
>> You've got good nuts now.
>> I think if Ozzy were to
propose marriage to Erik right
now, done deal.
>> I want to move the boat.
>> Okay.
>> To the back beach.
>> Oh, wow.
>> It makes way more sense to
have it on that side.
It will be fast.
>> They asked me to help move
the boat to the back beach.
We'd better be able to get back,
I know that, before it's
sundown.
Everybody knows, it's no secret,
I'm not a strong swimmer, but
being a team player, you think
you can get more fish on the
back beach, I'll help you row to
the back beach.
When we get way out in the
middle of nowhere, and Ozzy
decides, "well, the reef is
right there, come on, we can get
really big fish at the reef,"
I'm nervous as hell.
I've never been out that far in
the ocean in a little wooden
boat.
>> I can see!
I can see what you can see!
Yeah, you.
>> Just trust me for a little
bit.
There could be a giant clam out
there that will feed us for the
rest of the time.
Maybe there will be a pearl in
there I can give Cirie for
paddling out here.
>> Ozzy is about numero uno, and
that's Oscar.
Yay, reef, reef.
>> Cirie!
Oh, you're unhappy!
>> So they'll have this little
reef adventure at my expense
today, but it won't happen
again.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
Airai getting your first look at
the new Malakal tribe.
Chet voted out at the last
tribal council.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: This is a traditional
Micronesian money stone.
For years, these stones were the
currency in Micronesia.
The larger the stone, the more
value.
Today they're a part of your
challenge.
For today's challenge, four of
you will be blindfolded.
The other two tribe members will
use verbal direction to guide
you as you push a giant money
stone through the jungle course.
Along the way, you will crush
the tiles at four stations
revealing a pair of smaller
money stones.
You'll then use those eight
stones to solve a rotating cog
puzzle.
First tribe to get it right wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Close your eyes and
imagine you're under a beautiful
refreshing waterfall.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, god!
>> JEFF: And you're cleaning
your body, and you're washing
your hair.
>> Oh, you got to...
>> That's your reward.
It is the herbal essence great
escape spa.
The winning tribe will be taken
to an island.
You'll have plenty of products.
You can wash up, get clean.
When you're finished, a nice
little snack to round out the
day.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Absolutely.
>> JEFF: In addition, the
winning tribe will send one
member from the losing tribe to
Exile Island.
You will also choose somebody,
again, from your own tribe to
join them.
Airai, you have one extra
member.
Who is going to sit this one
out?
>> I am.
>> JEFF: All right, Natalie,
take a spot over here.
Give the rest of you a minute to
strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, guys.
Come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on.
Keep coming.
>> Okay, follow my voice, follow
my voice.
Keep coming straight.
Keep coming, keep coming, keep
coming.
>> Come on, straight, straight.
Pivot to your left, to your
left.
The other way!
>> That's right.
>> Cirie, you're backwards.
Right, right, right.
>> Okay, stop!
Come across!
>> JEFF: Malakal is through
their first tile.
>> Keep going.
Okay, you're at the thing.
You feel it?
You've got to pivot left a
little.
Okay, straight.
Keep going!
Keep going.
Straight.
There you go.
You broke the stone.
>> JEFF: Airai is through the
first tile.
They have their first two money
stones.
>> To your left.
No, no, I'm sorry.
To your right.
>> Okay, now toward the left,
toward the left, toward the
left, toward the left.
>> Now back up.
Just back straight up.
>> A little right, a little
right.
Right.
Keep going, keep going, keep
going, keep going.
>> Okay, now straight over it
this way!
Got it, got it!
>> JEFF: Malakal smashes their
second tile.
>> Perfect, perfect!
Straight.
Okay, you broke it.
>> JEFF: Airai smashes their
second tile.
>> Over here.
Come on, come on!
>> Haul ass!
Go, go, go!
>> Stop!
Now come forward.
Slow, slow.
>> JEFF: Malakal lined up for
their third tile, and they have
it.
>> Over here!
>> JEFF: One tile left to break
before you start working on that
puzzle.
>> Come straight towards me,
straight toward me.
It didn't break.
Back it up.
Back it up, back it up.
>> Which way do we move it now?
>> Shut up and listen!
>> Pivot right, pivot right.
Now come straight through, come
straight through.
Yes.
>> JEFF: Airai smashes their
third tile.
>> Turn to your right a little
more.
Straight across, right now!
>> JEFF: Cirie not messing
around.
They're straight through.
Malakal has all eight.
Start working on the puzzle.
Three people.
>> Okay, you're almost at the
last one guys.
Keep coming straight.
Okay, now, perfect.
You should be able to come
straight through.
Yes, good job, good job, good
job.
>> JEFF: Airai has their eighth
and final money stone.
Start working on the puzzle.
It's Erik, Cirie, and Ozzy
working for Malakal.
Eliza, Kathy, and James working
the puzzle for Airai.
This puzzle will only go
together one way.
That does not mean certain
pieces won't fit in and appear
to be right and still be wrong.
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: It is trial and error.
>> There we go.
>> I don't think you have to
force it that much.
>> JEFF: James hoping it's in
the right spot.
>> This one right here.
This one right here.
This is right.
>> JEFF: Eliza, James, Kathy,
not making much progress.
>> That's it, that's it, Ozzy.
>> JEFF: Malakal thinks they're
getting closer.
>> We need one more.
Do we got it?
>> We got it!
Jeff!
>> JEFF: Malakal thinks they
have it.
Malakal wins reward!
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: Malakal,
congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> JEFF: Nice big reward coming
your way.
First things first-- choosing
somebody from Airai to go to
Exile Island.
>> Jason.
>> JEFF: Jason, you're going
back to Exile Island.
Now, Malakal, you have to choose
somebody from your own tribe to
go to Exile Island, which means
they will not go on the spa
reward.
>> Oh!
>> Wow!
>> Can you take one for the
team?
>> Me?
Oh, god.
I'm going to Exile.
>> JEFF: All right, Tracy,
Jason, get your stuff.
The boat's waiting on you.
Airai, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Malakal, come get your stuff.
The boat is waiting for you.
>> Yeah!
Oh, damn!
( cheering )
>> Muffins.
>> Cookies!
>> It was so funny to see Erik.
For one, he was experiencing a
reward for the first time since
he's been here.
>> I am so happy right now.
>> It was really cool.
I mean, he's like a wide-eyed
kid in a candy store.
It made me feel proud that we
were able to win and bring him
in and let him experience this.
>> That was nice.
>> Yeah.
>> What is that?
I think that's our shower right
there.
>> Yeah.
>> You want to go shower?
>> I'll come scrub your back
when you're halfway through.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Ami, come on!
>> I'm getting naked.
I don't care.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Everyone, get naked.
>> My goodness.
Ooh-wee.
I don't know.
I just looked over and there's,
like, a couple of pair of boobs,
and Ozzy's head smack dab in the
middle.
I'm like, "Okay."
The only thing funnier was Erik
drooling from the sight.
( laughs )
Hey, to each his own.
If you feel free like that, then
by all means, get free.
I just wouldn't do it.
>> Oh, oh, man.
This is as perfect as I could
have ever hoped for.
>> This came on so fast.
>> It's a freaking mon-freaking-
soon.
>> It just came out of nowhere.
>> It's completely different.
You watch this show at home, and
when they show the rain, they
show it for, like, 30 seconds.
They're not showing that you're
standing in the rain or trying
to sleep while you're being
rained on for five, six hours
straight, non-stop.
We had to stand out there, and
James went out in the rain and
caught a clam, and we had to sit
around and eat a raw clam,
because there's no fire, and
you're all just digging in it
with your hands like you're
animals.
>> You guys okay if I put a
little on my lemon?
>> You people are disgusting.
I was just talking about how I
think...
>> And it's full of sand, and
it's full of dirt.
And the coconut you're cleaning
falls on the ground, but you
don't care.
You just put it back in, because
it's food.
And it's just savagery.
It's like you're cavemen, you
know?
Never in a million years would I
ever do this twice.
>> Is it scary in there?
>> It just rained, and it
rained, and we crawled way down
into the cave.
And it's miserable.
And it's awful.
And it's dirty.
And you don't even know what's
dead and crawling.
Son of a bitch!
We sleep in the caves with bats
and rats and crawly things.
>> Ow!
>> It's hard to explain that
experience, that it's just...
it's just so uncomfortable.
It's so unpleasant.
And I said it myself the other
day, "This is the stupidest
thing I've ever done in my life.
This is the dumbest thing I've
ever done."
Well, when I woke up this
morning, I hadn't gotten any
sleep.
Again, we were in the cave.
It rained all night.
And I was looking for some kind
of strength, and I couldn't find
it.
I was thinking of putting some
wood on the beach, but I don't
know how high the tide will come
in.
Can I have one more hug, one
more?
I need one more hug to get me
through the day.
I'm just so out of it, James.
>> It's okay.
Everybody has their days.
>> You know, I was trying to
send... it sounds so stupid.
I was trying to send, like,
vibes to my daughter, Maddie.
You know, "Can you hear me?
You can feel me?
I need your help.
I need your help to help me
through this because I can't do
this."
And I couldn't... I couldn't
feel her.
I can't feel my family.
I don't know what it is, but I'm
just downward spiraling, and I
can't take another minute, I
can't.
I can't.
I know it's sunny, it's
beautiful, it's like, "Ooh,"
But I can't.
I can't be here one more minute.
I can't take it.
And I just want you guys to be
okay and not hate me for it.
I just can't take it one more
minute, I can't.
>> You have to be 100% sure.
>> I'm 100% sure.
I can't.
I can't do it anymore.
>> Not to make light of how
you're feeling, but we all feel
like that today.
We're all going bananas.
And I'm not trying to make light
of what's going on in your head.
>> It's a tough day.
>> It's just a hard day.
>> Let's walk in the sun a
little bit.
>> Come here, come here.
>> I want to go now.
>> It's okay.
I want them to come and get a
boat and pick me up and take me
away, because I can't do this
anymore.
I can't.
I tried so hard.
>> I know, sweetie, I know.
>> I tried so hard.
>> I know.
>> I think it was a horrible
night, and I think it just took
its toll on Kathy.
Kathy just really got in her
head today.
Like, everything just compiled
and built up one upon another,
and she's just severely
depressed.
>> I just want to go.
>> She just came up to us on the
beach, bawling, crying, and told
us that she can't take another
day out here and she has to go.
Like, she's done.
She's quitting the game.
>> JEFF: Hello, guys.
>> Hi.
>> JEFF: So, well, I got word
that you wanted to see me.
You've had enough?
What's going on?
It's 19 days you've been out
here.
>> I know.
>> JEFF: Let me come over... let
me just come over here.
>> I kind of sat on the boat for
a while today, and I couldn't
feel my family, you know?
And I'm never leaving my baby
girl or husband again ever for
this amount of time, ever again.
>> JEFF: So what is it that...
you've had a tough time out
here.
You've had as tough... you've
had it as tough as anybody with
all the time on Exile.
But you've weathered all that.
So you want to leave, you're
leaving.
There's no... I'm not here to
talk you into staying.
That's for sure.
>> Right.
>> JEFF: I just want to
understand it.
>> I was doing it for everybody
else.
Doing it for my husband.
Doing it for my sister who wants
to live vicariously through me.
I don't want to hurt these
people.
So I want to stay to help them.
This is, like, the first
decision I've made that's, like,
for me, you know, because I
don't want to let anybody down.
I don't want anybody to hate me.
I don't want anybody to think
that I'm quitting.
>> JEFF: This adventure means
different things to different
people.
It represents different things
to different people.
You've certainly given it your
best.
>> Yeah.
Oh, god.
>> JEFF: And all's going to be
okay.
Ready to get out of here?
>> I am.
>> JEFF: Let's get your stuff.
>> I'm sorry, guys.
>> Don't apologize.
>> I'm sorry.
>> You know, Kathy's been
through a lot, and most of it is
she lost most of her motivation.
So what's the point of going
through the suffering?
>> It was nice to get to know
you these last couple of days.
>> She just said she's had
enough, and she's quitting.
Which is sad, but still and all,
I mean, it's up to her.
You can't fault her.
You can't be upset with her.
Hope she has a good trip, and
I'm sure I'll see her again.
>> JEFF: So the Airai tribe is
down to six in spite of winning
challenges.
Game continues.
See you soon.
>> Bye.
>> Kathy leaving, it's sad, but
at the same time, life goes on
here, and there's a reality to
the fact that the sun is going
down, and we haven't had water
in three days, and we haven't
had a cooked meal because we
haven't had fire.
You know, so Survivor continues
for the rest of us.
>> I think you got a dose of who
Oscar really is with the boat
ride yesterday.
And...
>> I'm starting to see that.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> He's kind of arrogant.
>> You think?
>> Kind of bothering me.
>> Hmm.
Amanda got to see how there's a
selfish, arrogant part to Ozzy.
>> It's so sad.
Very sad.
>> And if I got that out of the
trip, then, okay, I can suck it
up, because there was a benefit
to it-- letting her see, you
know, Ozzy is about Ozzy.
>> I don't know.
Like, I've been trying to figure
out if people really think Ozzy
is, like, the best thing in the
world or if they're just
playing.
>> Did you hear Erik?
"Oh, my god, if he wasn't here
we'd die."
It's like, "Shut up, Erik."
How can we vote Erik, though?
How many of us is it?
Because Ozzy is not going to
vote Erik.
He's kind of in love with Erik
right now.
They climbed that coconut tree.
And because he just worships the
ground that he walks on, he'll
never get rid of Erik.
>> I think it's the best move to
make.
>> To get rid of Erik?
>> Maybe.
>> Ozzy's not going to do it.
>> We just have to let him think
he's in complete control.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys.
Malakal, getting your first look
at the new Airai tribe.
Kathy has left the game.
>> Kathy?
>> What?
>> JEFF: We'll bring Jason and
Tracy in from Exile.
I'll explain what happened.
>> Well, hello!
>> Hi.
>> Hey.
>> JEFF: Let me kitchen
everybody up on what's going on.
Yesterday, Kathy sent word that
she wanted out of the game.
I went over to Airai's camp.
She said, "I've had enough.
I need to go."
We packed up her belongings.
She quit.
Both tribes at six.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: First things first.
Give it up, Eliza.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
On my go, one member of each
tribe will race across a
floating bridge carrying one end
of a piece of rope.
When you reach the platform,
you'll clip the rope into a
large puzzle piece, and then
hang on as the rest of the tribe
will crank a giant winch,
pulling you and the puzzle piece
back to shore.
Once you've collected all five
puzzle pieces, two tribe members
will unfold those bundles and
use the pieces to solve a puzzle
in the form of a perfect square.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: I'll give you a minute
to strategize, we'll get
started.
Eliza and Ozzy first off.
Here we go, for immunity,
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, baby, go!
>> Come on, Ozzy!
>> You got it Eliza!
>> Go, Eliza!
>> You got it, girl!
>> Come on, Ozzy!
Go, go, go!
>> JEFF: Ozzy first to the
puzzle piece.
Eliza right there.
>> Go!
>> JEFF: Airai taking a long
time to get going.
Ozzy's back with the puzzle
piece.
Next person going!
Ozzy's going to go again.
Airai lost a lot of time right
off the bat.
Next person.
Jason now for Airai.
>> Come on, Ozzy!
>> JEFF: Ozzy at the second
bundle of puzzle pieces.
Ozzy with a big lead for
Malakal.
Jason struggling.
>> Erik!
Go, Erik.
It's you next.
Push.
Come on, push.
>> JEFF: Erik on the course.
Malakal has three bundles left.
>> Go!
>> JEFF: Jason now getting a
ride back with Airai's second
bundle.
Erik struggling on the bridge.
Airai now making up some time.
Erik reaches the platform.
Parvati on the course.
>> Come on, Parv!
You got it, girl!
>> JEFF: We are tied, two
bundles each.
>> Yeah!
>> JEFF: Parvati struggling on
the bridge.
>> Good job, Parv!
Keep it up, girl!
>> JEFF: Erik back with the
third puzzle piece for Malakal.
Only two puzzle pieces left.
>> You got it, girl.
>> Almost there!
>> JEFF: Ozzy having no trouble
on this bridge.
Parvati reaches the end.
She's clipped in.
Parvati now being dragged in.
Ozzy reaches the end of the
platform quickly.
>> There you go!
>> JEFF: Ozzy like he's on a
boogie board.
Ozzy's going to go again.
Malakal with their fourth puzzle
piece.
Parvati back with the third
puzzle piece for Airai.
Natalie heading out on the
course.
Malakal leads 4-3.
>> You got it, Nat!
>> Come on, Ozzy!
>> JEFF: Ozzy heads out for that
fifth and final puzzle piece for
Malakal.
Natalie losing a lot of time for
Airai.
Ozzy's coming back with that
fifth and final piece.
Natalie's at the platform and
clipped in.
>> Hold on!
>> JEFF: Malakal pulling him
back.
Ozzy really working it like it's
a board.
Malakal has all five pieces.
Go!
Two puzzle makers.
>> Go, go, go!
>> JEFF: Amanda and Cirie start
working on the puzzle for
Malakal.
Eliza heads out for that fifth
and final puzzle piece per
Airai.
Malakal already working on that
puzzle with a big lead.
This puzzle will form a perfect
square.
>> Go, go, go!
>> JEFF: Eliza clips in to the
fifth puzzle piece for Airai.
The quicker you get started, the
faster you will finish.
Eliza back with the final piece!
Go!
Jason and Eliza going to work on
the puzzle.
Amanda and Cirie working on the
puzzle for Malakal.
Immunity on the line.
>> You guys are doing great!
>> JEFF: These pieces are heavy,
going to be hard to move.
Jason and Eliza still untying.
>> It's okay, guys, get them
untied.
>> We've got them untied.
We just need to get them out.
Help me get them out.
>> JEFF: Malakal with a big lead
already starting to work on this
puzzle.
Eliza and Jason have all five of
their pieces untied.
They're starting to work on
forming the puzzle.
>> Use that one.
>> This one?
>> Right here, yeah.
Push that one over, Amanda!
>> JEFF: Amanda and Cirie now
starting to struggle a bit.
Jason and Eliza have a different
strategy, spreading all the piss
out, looking for patterns.
>> Help her pull this one!
Help her pull this one!
>> JEFF: Cirie and Amanda really
slowing down.
Eliza and Jason starting to make
a little progress.
>> This one at the bottom?
>> Yeah, yeah.
Flip it around.
There you go.
>> Turn it, turn it!
Right here, right here.
>> That one might be the center.
>> JEFF: Cirie and Amanda taking
their time.
>> That one right there, that
one right there.
Right in the middle.
>> JEFF: Eliza and Jason trying
to shove one last piece in.
Will it fit?
Is it right?
Airai wins immunity!
Airai, congratulations.
Immunity is yours once again.
For the third straight time,
Airai wins immunity, safe from
tribal council.
Malakal, tribal council tonight,
where one of you is going home.
Grab your stuff.
See you there.
Airai, head out.
Nice job.
>> Hey, Oz, I'm so sorry about
the puzzle.
I feel like crap about it.
>> Yeah.
It was so easy.
>> So then who do we choose?
>> I think it just makes more
sense if Tracy...
>> Ozzy is wanting Erik to stay
because he's got a good
relationship going with Erik,
but I just feel like I can work
more with Tracy.
She's more into the game, and
being third or fourth among
Cirie, Ozzy, and Amanda is
something that's definitely
always on my mind.
Could I betray him if it comes
down to that?
Sometimes you have to pull the
dirty cards to stay in the game.
Let me tell you what's
happening.
The girls want to get rid of
Erik.
Ozzy wants to get rid of you.
It was his idea to send you to
Exile.
>> I know.
>> And so if we can get Ozzy to
vote for you and us three girls
to vote for, Erik, then you, me,
and Erik can vote for Ozzy and
get Ozzy out of here.
>> The plan that Tracy and I
talked about is talk Amanda and
Cirie into voting for Erik,
which they want to do anyway.
Tell them that I'll vote with
them.
Go for that.
We all three say we're voting
for Erik.
Ozzy doesn't know, and doesn't
want to vote for Erik, so he'll
vote for Tracy, thinking we're
all going to vote for Tracy.
Well, underneath all of that,
Tracy, Erik, and I are going to
vote for Ozzy, and just take
Ozzy out at the knees.
>> Mm-hmm.
You're next after me.
If you think you are.
>> In order to pull off voting
out Ozzy at this point, we have
to either pull in Cirie and
Amanda.
If this doesn't work out, I have
to vote Tracy.
If I voted Ozzy with Tracy, they
would flip out, and I would be
so done, whatever came next.
>> Well, I know Ozzy wants me.
But I'd like to stay.
And you got to think right now
what you're going to do.
Would you rather go up against
me or would you rather go up
against Ozzy?
Would you rather go up against
Erik or would you rather go up
against me?
As long as you two say that
that's good.
>> So you feel like Erik, right,
because of...
>> Well, yeah.
Are you?
Do you think that's the best
decision?
>> I'm just nervous about what
Ozzy might have planned on the
other side with Erik and those
girls.
>> If I was definitely set on
wanting Erik out tonight, he'd
be gone tonight.
I guarantee you.
But I don't know at this point
if I will be able to turn on
Ozzy or not.
If I go against Ozzy, then I can
pretty much kiss that
relationship good-bye.
I mean, there are so many people
that you have to vote out.
You're going to hurt someone's
feelings in this game.
It's inevitable.
>> Don't look at me!
>> If Cirie and Amanda don't
vote with me, there's a whole
other path that could be taken.
I'm kind of going both ways in
my head still.
Am I going to take Ozzy out, or
am I going to stick with these
people that I've known from the
beginning and vote out one of
the fans?
Tonight's decision is a very big
decision.
It could change the game in a
serious way.
>> JEFF: Let's get straight to
it.
This tribe is obviously in
trouble.
You've lost three straight
immunity challenges.
The only reason you're even
halfway in it is because of odd
circumstances-- Penner having to
be medically pulled out of the
game, and Kathy deciding to
quit.
Tracy, who is leading this
tribe?
>> Ozzy.
Ozzy is leading this tribe.
I mean, Ozzy was the first one
that looked at me and said, "You
need to go to Exile Island for
the tribe."
Ozzy tells us who is going to
compete, when you're going to
eat, and what you're going to
eat.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, you had a big
reaction when Tracy said you're
the leader.
>> Oh, yeah, just... it's
ridiculous.
If I'm the leader of this tribe,
I haven't known about it.
I do what needs to get done at
certain times, but I really
don't feel like I'm the leader
of the tribe.
And I definitely don't feel like
I'm deciding who eats what when.
That doesn't make any sense, and
doesn't jibe with me at all.
>> JEFF: Cirie, somebody's got
to be leading the tribe to one
degree or another.
>> In a way I kind of see where
Tracy's coming from.
I'm not saying that Ozzy is the
leader of the tribe, but just
about 90% of everything that we
do, everyone checks with Ozzy
first.
>> JEFF: Erik, do you see what
everybody's talking about, the
dynamics right now?
>> There's a conflict going on.
There's a conflict in this
tribe.
And, I mean, I understand Ozzy's
point.
Nobody wants to be the leader,
but things need to get done.
Things need to happen, and he's
doing so much for this tribe.
If he was gone, we would fall
apart faster than we are right
now.
>> JEFF: Ami, there are two
different approaches this tribe
could take right now-- short-
term thinking, which is, "We
need to win challenges."
Long-term thinking is, "I need
to start getting rid of people
who could beat me in this game."
Take me down that line.
>> Well, you always have to be
looking out for, "Which one of
these people is going to be the
biggest threat to me, and when's
the best time to get rid of
them?"
And you've got to play your
cards when it makes the most
sense.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, when you hear Ami
talking about getting rid of the
people more threatening, make
you a little concerned?
>> Oh, yeah, it does.
I'm not that naive to think that
people don't want me gone even
if they need me to win
challenges.
I'm still going to give it my
all, and I'm still going to be
loyal to the people that I've
said I'm going to be loyal to.
Nothing's going to change that.
So if I'm a threat and people
want to get rid of me, you know,
that's one strategy.
But the other strategy is they
can be with me and we can try
and go to the end together.
>> JEFF: Tracy, why keep you
tonight?
>> I think I'd be a better tribe
member than somebody's that's
going to demolish you if you do
go to the merge.
And I think that's that needs to
be a thought that all these
people need to think about.
I would be less of a threat than
Ozzy to Ami, to Amanda, to
Cirie, than Ozzy.
It's just as simple as that.
It's black and white.
There's no gray.
>> JEFF: All right, let's get to
it.
It is time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
>> You said you were honest, and
that's bull.
>> This is because you wanted me
out.
Good player.
No hard feelings.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now wouldn't time to do
so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Tracy.
Ozzy.
One vote Tracy, one vote Ozzy.
Tracy.
Two votes Tracy, one vote Ozzy.
That's three votes Tracy, one
vote Ozzy.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Fans Versus
Favorites, Tracy.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Tracy, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, tonight's vote was big for
one simple reason-- you've got
to start winning some
challenges.
Hopefully you made the right
choice.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
Ami and Cirie go on the warpath.
On Airai, Parvati makes new
friends.
>> You and Alexis, me and
Amanda, final four.
>> JEFF: And the injuries
continue to pile up.
Erik takes a hard hit.
He's out!
>> Going up against the
favorites was quite difficult.
Ozzy's a wonderful player in
this game.
He is manipulative and he is
strategic.
He will definitely take the rest
of the tribe down.
They need to get rid of him ASAP
or else they don't stand a
chance.
I wish I could have stayed in
longer.
I went out kicking.
I did everything I could, and
I'm just grateful to be here.