>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: ...despite winning
challenges...
Airai wins!
...the Airai tribe was losing
players.
First, Jonathan.
>> I can't be here one more
minute.
>> PROBST: Then Kathy.
On Exile Island, Ozzy found the
hidden immunity idol and
replaced it with a fake one as a
decoy, which was discovered by
Jason.
>> There we go, baby.
I guess this is the hidden
immunity idol.
>> PROBST: At Malakal, Ozzy
practically adopted Erik.
>> They're like The Lion King--
the father, when he was teaching
the cub.
>> PROBST: So when his tribe was
facing tribal council, he knew
exactly who he wanted to vote
out.
>> I don't think that there's
any argument for keeping Tracy.
>> PROBST: But Ami saw a chance
to turn against the favorites
and go after Ozzy.
>> Sometimes you have to pull
the dirty cards to stay in the
game.
>> PROBST: Tracy also went after
Ozzy, warning everyone that he's
not only the tribe leader but
the biggest threat.
>> I think I'd be a better tribe
member than somebody that's
going to demolish you if you do
go to the merge.
>> PROBST: But in the end, Ami
sided with the favorites.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites,
Tracy.
And Tracy was sent home, leaving
Erik as the only remaining fan
on the Malakal tribe.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Tonight at tribal, Tracy went
home.
I feel lucky to be here still.
I feel really, really lucky to
still be here and have a shot at
this game.
But I am scared to death,
because I'm the last fan left,
and I don't think I see any
leeway with these favorites.
I feel like I'm the next to go,
no matter what happens now in
the future.
>> Here, scratch my back.
>> Tribal council was a little
bit of an eye opener.
Tracy described me as the
leader.
I really don't think that I'm
the leader.
I just think that I've got a lot
of good opinions and a lot of
know-how when it comes to
surviving out here, and people
respect that.
Even though I think I'm a
valuable asset, I'm going to
have a giant target on my back.
And that's the kind of situation
that I want to avoid.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Careful, Ami.
>> Get him!
>> Come on!
No, no, no!
Go in there!
Nice work.
All right.
This will give a girl a heart
attack.
That was fun this morning.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Ozzy's like, "Did you guys
get anything?"
"No, not really, just eight
crabs."
>> You guys did awesome!
>> We're the crab warriors.
>> That's crazy!
Girl, give me some sugar.
>> Well, don't let it get to you
yet.
>> Well, who cares about that
stuff?
Don't worry about that.
>> Like, last night, Tracy was
trying everything in her power
to get you to get voted off.
She was coming to me.
She was coming to Cirie.
She's, like, trying everything.
Who cares?
I stopped anything crazy from
happening.
Yeah.
>> Tracy is sneaky.
>> It's not that big of a deal,
you know.
It didn't happen, and it's not
going to happen, so don't worry
about it.
Okay?
>> This morning, Ami ended up
telling me that she was
approached by Tracy and asked to
vote for me, but she said, you
know, that she wasn't going to
do that and she's on my side.
>> You're not in any danger.
Like, let it go.
>> It's just the tribal council
last night was kind of like...
>> I'm not leaving you.
>> But Ami's a little too
adamant about that.
And as much as she says she's on
my side, I'm starting to get
uneasy feelings.
>> I was dreaming about pizza
that I just put in an oven.
>> Fluffy on top.
>> Yeah.
Mm!
I just don't want another
bite of coconut.
I just don't.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Ah, you got him!
Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
James!
>> What?
>> He caught a rat!
>> I cannot believe you just
caught a rat.
>> Oh, poor guy.
Get the shish kebab and just,
like...
>> Oh.
>> There's nothing on him,
though, really.
I think I'm going to feel a
little bad eating the rat.
You know, he's a small guy.
There's not much meat on there.
But you know, out here, we're in
the bush, and it's survival of
the fittest.
So yeah, I'm going to dig into
the rat and give it a shot.
We'll stick a skewer through
him, barbecue him up.
Nobody has eaten a rat since the
first season of Survivor, so
it's kind of cool.
I'll be able to bring that
tradition back.
>> Ew, look at his tail.
He's so yuck.
>> I sure the tail is delicious.
>> Have you ever had a rat
before?
>> Never.
>> I think Jason's been trying
to impress the favorites ever
since the switch up.
It's not working, though.
I think he's a loser.
>> This is a nightmare over
here.
This island sucks.
There's nothing but rock.
You don't have enough beach
area.
You can't go anywhere.
There's nothing.
It's like pretty much a barren
land.
You could live on Malakal.
Over here, this is where they
bring the criminals.
>> I just want to go back to
Amanda.
>> I just want to go back.
>> I want to go back to Amanda
and Cirie and Oz.
>> This sucks.
The original Malakal alliance
was supposed to be myself,
Amanda, Parvati, Ozzy, and
Cirie.
But over here, it's just Parvati
and I.
So, I mean, I'm at my wit's end.
>> Are you nervous?
>> Not now.
And if we can make it back to
the merge, we're fine.
>> That would suck.
At this point, six people are
left in this tribe, so we need a
very solid four to go into the
merge.
So me and James are really going
to have to pull in two more
people, you know, in order to
remain in a strong position in
this tribe.
This is how I came into this
game, to play in stages.
Like, the first stage was,
clearly, before the mix-up, when
it was fans versus favorites,
and just to get through that,
the first couple of votes.
And then we have the mix-up.
So we have to play through this
segment to get to the merge.
I just feel like I would feel
safe if it was you and Alexis,
me and James locked up at four,
a block of four.
>> Yeah.
I will work with you.
>> Okay.
>> I think that James, we can
still win immunity.
>> I think with James, we're
fine until the merge.
And then once we get to the
merge, all of the targets are
going to be on the big guys.
Like, we're going to be able to
slip under because everyone's
going to be so threatened by the
big guys trying to get them out.
>> Ozzy, James.
>> Ozzy and James are probably
going to be the first to go.
>> I'm down.
>> I wouldn't see anything wrong
with it being y'all two, me, and
Amanda final four.
>> Yeah, how hot would that be?
>> You know?
I'm not going to win against
Ozzy, and I'm not going to win
against James.
There's no way.
I love them.
I love having them around, but I
don't want to go up against them
at the end.
So I might just go ahead and
pull in Alexis and Natalie and
take them with me and Amanda to
the four.
Everyone else, they're dead to
me.
>> Oh.
>> Oh, my God.
"Choose one player from the
Malakal tribe to sit out today's
immunity challenge.
The person you choose will be
sent to Exile Island, but they
will be returned to their
tribe's camp before tonight's
tribal council with individual
immunity."
Tonight's tribal council with
individual immunity?
"This individual's immunity is
good for tonight's tribal
council only.
Circle their name on this
parchment, seal it in the
envelope, and present it to Jeff
at the challenge."
>> Wow.
And so Tracy was voted out.
>> Yeah.
>> We just got tree mail and
found out that we have an
immunity challenge today, which
is kind of shocking, because we
just had an immunity challenge
yesterday.
We had to pick one member of the
Malakal tribe to sit out of
today's challenge and to get
individual immunity at tonight's
tribal council.
This is huge.
>> Whose name do you think
they'll be circling?
>> "Individual immunity is good
for tonight's tribal council
only.
Circle their name and seal the
envelope and present it to Jeff
at the challenge."
>> Wow.
>> Then we got this, like,
hanging like this.
And this piece says, "Life here
is like a balancing act with the
other tribe trying to knock you
down."
>> Oh, no!
>> "Win this one, you're safe
tonight, and it'll be your tribe
who's chowing down."
>> I think whoever wins the
immunity challenge gets to go to
a feast, and then the other
tribe has to go to tribal
council.
>> Not both, not both.
>> Right, right.
>> So...
>> Who do we want to sit out?
>> Whoever is their best
balancer.
>> If we go to tribal council
tonight and I don't have
immunity, I'm dead.
So I am hoping so much that I
get some form of immunity here
and survive this tribal council
tonight.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Airai, getting your first look
at the new Malakal tribe.
Tracy voted out at the last
tribal council.
You guys ready to get to it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: This morning in tree
mail, you were instructed to
select one member from the other
tribe to sit out of today's
immunity challenge.
This person will not
participate.
Instead, they will go to Exile
Island with individual immunity.
Here's what that means.
If their tribe loses and they
have to go to tribal council,
they cannot be voted out.
That immunity is good only for
tonight's tribal council, only
if your tribe goes to tribal
council.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You guys both made
your selections?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: I'll come get them.
To sit out of today's challenge,
Airai selected Ozzy.
To sit out of the challenge,
Malakal selected-- originally,
it was James.
They changed it to Alexis.
Ami, tell me about that.
Why the change of heart?
>> She seems like she could
balance, and it seemed like it
was about balance, so we decided
to get rid of Alexis.
>> PROBST: Alexis, Ozzy, get
your stuff.
Boat's waiting on you.
Right down there.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> How about what we're playing
for?
>> PROBST: How about first you
give me immunity back?
How about that?
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
On my go, one tribe member at a
time will attempt to navigate an
obstacle course while members of
the other tribe attempt to knock
you off by swinging heavy canvas
bags.
When you reach the end, you'll
grab a flag, try to make your
way back.
If you fall off at any point
along the way, you have to make
your way back to the start and
the next person goes.
First tribe to collect five
flags wins.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: Winning tribe,
immunity.
In addition, pizza and beer
delivered to your camp this
afternoon.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Pizza.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Airai, you have one
extra member-- sitting somebody
out.
Who's it going to be?
>> I'm going to sit out.
>> PROBST: Parvati, take a spot
on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
Running the course for Airai,
Eliza and Jason.
Swinging the bags for Airai,
Natalie and James.
For Malakal, running the course,
Erik and Amanda.
Swinging the bags, Ami and
Cirie.
For immunity and reward in the
form of pizza and beer.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Erik leaps across the stepping
stones, makes his way across the
barrel, missing the bags.
James tries to hit him, just
misses.
Erik and Jason both across the
first part of this course.
>> Come on, Erik!
>> Good job, Jason!
>> PROBST: You got to get all
the way back while missing those
bags.
James launches and hits Erik on
the head, but it's not enough.
Erik hanging on, almost falls
off, but doesn't.
Nice save!
>> Come on, Erik!
>> Good job, Jason.
>> PROBST: Jason's across for
Airai with one.
Erik's across.
Eliza falls.
Amanda falls off for Malakal.
Erik once again leaps across the
stepping stones.
Nobody having any luck with the
bags yet.
Erik working the balance beam.
He eludes the bags.
Jason coming back with the
second flag for Airai.
We are tied 1-1.
>> Come on, Erik, you got it.
>> PROBST: Jason having no
trouble.
Airai now leads 2-1.
>> Come on, Eliza!
>> PROBST: Erik coming back with
that second flag.
>> Go, go, go.
>> PROBST: Erik back with the
second flag for Malakal.
We're tied, 2-2.
Amanda hanging on.
Eliza falls off.
She's got to head back.
Amanda with a nice save.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Amanda trying to
tippytoe around that barrel.
Amanda takes a hard hit and
survives.
Amanda's halfway there.
>> Get him, get him, get him!
>> PROBST: Jason right behind
her.
We are tied 2-2.
>> Come on, Amanda!
>> PROBST: Amanda back at the
balance beam.
Bags being tossed.
James aiming for Amanda, just
misses.
Cirie just misses on Jason.
Amanda, slow going, but no
trouble for Jason.
>> Good job, Amanda!
>> PROBST: Amanda's across.
We're tied 3-3.
Erik leaps again.
Eliza's there.
Eliza's got it.
>> Good job, girl, good job.
>> PROBST: We are tied 3-3, neck
and neck.
>> Just focus, Erik.
Go!
>> PROBST: Erik across the
barrels, across the beam, just
misses a bag from Natalie.
Eliza heading back with that
fourth flag for Airai.
>> Get her!
Get her!
>> PROBST: Eliza back with the
fourth flag.
Got to get across the stepping
stones.
Airai leads 4-3.
Erik across.
We're tied 4-4.
One flag left for both tribes.
>> Come on, Erik!
>> PROBST: Erik going back out
and takes a hard hit!
He's out.
>> Come on, Amanda!
>> PROBST: Erik smashed hard
against the platform.
Amanda falls off.
>> Get him, Ami!
>> PROBST: Jason all the way to
the other end of the course, no
trouble.
You've got to knock Jason off.
Erik's going to go again.
It's not going to matter.
Jason with that fifth and final
flag for Airai.
>> Pizza and beer!
( cheering )
>> PROBST: Airai wins immunity
and reward!
>> Good job, guys.
Good job.
>> Oh, my God!
Oh!
>> PROBST: Airai, for the fourth
straight time, immunity.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: No tribal council
tonight.
Nobody going home from this
tribe.
Pizza and beer delivered to your
camp this afternoon.
Malakal, here's what's going to
happen.
Ozzy will return to your camp
before tribal council.
He cannot be voted for, which
means one of the four of you are
going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
I'll see you at tribal.
>> Are you guys okay?
Who took that really hard fall?
>> Erik.
>> Where did you hit?
>> My chest.
>> Are you okay?
>> No.
>> Let's see.
>> That hurt like crazy.
That challenge today was rough.
I mean, that was tough without
Ozzy there today.
I tried my damnedest, because
that was my last real attempt, I
think, that I could have.
But it was not happening.
It hurts.
I'm not going to lie.
That was pretty bad.
>> I think Erik is a genuine,
good person.
I really wish we would have won
today, because I would have
loved to have seen Erik stay.
But I don't see any way out for
him right now.
I don't see any way out for him.
( cheering )
>> Yeah!
>> Good job, team!
>> How long we've been dying.
>> Those dreams paid off.
Dreams paid off.
>> Good job.
>> Thank you.
I'd definitely say I was the MVP
today.
I think I brought back four of
the five flags, and I had a
great time.
But right now, I definitely feel
scared about my position over
here.
Luckily, I hold the hidden
immunity idol.
But other than that, you know, I
can't really count on any
alliances.
And you know, I'm just going to
have to compete at 110% at every
challenge, or it could be the
end of the game for me.
>> Good job on that challenge.
Y'all were great.
>> Good job.
>> Jason and Eliza pretty much
tore up that course, and we won.
I think they both kind of know
they're on the outs, so they
both gave it their all at this
challenge, and they saved each
other.
And I am so happy.
I don't think I'll be having rat
for dinner tonight.
Pizza party!
Pizza party.
( cheering )
>> Pass the beer over!
>> Oh, yeah!
We've got a pizza party!
>> Thanks!
>> Thank you!
>> Well, our pizza delivery boat
pulled up, and we had four
pizzas, and we also got a little
basket with garlic bread and a
bucket of beer in ice.
We're just... we're in heaven
right now.
Can't stop smiling.
>> Oh, that's what I want.
>> I want that one.
>> I'm so happy.
>> Oh, my God.
I don't... I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
>> Leverage, leverage.
No, don't pull.
Give it here.
>> Maybe there's an opener in
there.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> Cheers.
Cheers.
>> How amazing is this?
>> Today was a great day.
>> Good day 21.
>> So we're right here.
The fourth clue basically says
that...
>> It's back on this island?
>> Well, I'm not sure.
I spent hours searching this
part of the beach, but the
fourth clue says...
>> ...go back to the beginning.
>> ...it's under a rock.
I'm back at Exile with Alexis,
and I have the hidden immunity
idol already, but, I mean, I'm
here, so I want to find out if
somebody else found the immunity
idol-- the fake one, that is.
>> I feel like we're digging for
buried treasure.
>> Yeah.
Maybe this other little
outcropping over here.
This is over your head.
>> See, that's what I was
thinking, a tree or something
like that.
Ha-ha, someone's taken the bait.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Someone has taken my fake hidden
immunity idol.
I don't know who, but it's gone.
It's not here.
Who's it going to be?
Who is going to be tricked by
Ozzy?
>> Oh, Amanda.
Why can't we win?
>> I never lost so many times in
my life.
>> It's been forever.
>> It's sad.
>> But at the same time, you
have to remember Erik's a gamer.
>> He's competitive, man.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I still remember when he
dropped me on my freaking head.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Like, he's different in
challenges than he is here.
>> Oh, definitely.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> I want to stay in this game
very badly.
I've seen so many seasons of
this show.
It's killing me right now that
I'm this close to maybe making
the next level, making the next
set of alliances that can lead
me to the end of this game.
I feel like I'm on my last legs,
though.
I mean, all the fans are dead in
this tribe.
All the favorites have the
control.
But I'm trying to work with what
I have, and I'm pretty desperate
right now.
How well do you guys trust Ami?
>> Huh?
>> How well do you guys trust
Ami?
>> I don't know.
Why?
>> Because she's been trying to
get something together with
Airai since probably Joel left.
And when Chet was here, she
wanted to go with us to vote one
of you guys.
And then when it was just Tracy,
me, and her, she tried to sway
one of you guys, and that didn't
happen, so Tracy left.
( laughter )
She's told me about different
alliances that you guys have
had.
She said that she was part of
Yau-Man's alliance, and she said
she had nowhere to go, and
that's why she came to me and
Chet and Tracy.
I really don't want to hurt her,
because I really like Ami a lot.
I like Ami a lot.
She's such a good person.
But this isn't about people
anymore.
>> Right, right.
>> This is about the game.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And I want you guys to know
that if you decide Ami, I'll be
in with that.
>> Wow.
You don't know who to trust
here.
You have Erik fighting for his
life, who will say anything
right now, who will sell his
soul to the devil to stay.
And then you have Ami, who has
proven time and time again that
she can't be trusted-- that I
can't trust her.
>> I'm trying to save my neck
here.
So that's why I do whatever.
That's all I have.
Take it, leave it, pretend it's
lies, whatever, but that's
everything that I've heard.
>> See, the problem is I don't
trust Ami, but I don't trust
Erik either.
So my dilemma is who do I trust
the least?
So I was walking down the beach,
and I came back to camp, and
there's Erik just spilling the
beans, just going out about
every single thing that's gone
down since the swap.
I don't feel like I've done
anything to hurt you, have you?
I've stuck by you 100%, and I
always will.
He's trying everything in his
right mind...
>> No, I understand.
I know.
And I don't blame him.
>> No, neither do I.
>> If I vote either Ami or Erik,
it's going to be risky either
way.
Erik probably still has his
alliance with the fans, and if
they could get Eliza, that could
be a problem.
But it's the same thing with
Ami.
She could grab Eliza and go with
Jason, Natalie, and Alexis and
cause problems.
So I don't know.
Just with all the skittishness
and all the...
>> Well, you guys, I was the
last one, period, to even be,
like, talked to about being with
you guys.
You guys didn't ever even ask
me.
>> I know, because we thought
you were with Eliza and those
guys.
>> Yeah, but I was.
>> I know.
>> And then after that...
>> So why would we then?
>> Well, yeah, but since then,
you guys have never come
together and really said, "Okay,
Ami, we want you to be really a
part of this and totally into
this; like, we're watching your
back, no matter what."
I want to stick with you guys
the whole way and feel like I'm
part of you guys.
>> Right.
>> But nobody has really said,
"Hey, Ami, we want to fight with
you."
>> Well, we want to fight with
you.
>> Okay, thanks.
>> We don't know Erik like we
know Ami.
Like, we know we can't trust
Ami, and it's almost better with
the devil you know rather than
the devil you don't know.
I feel like we should have,
like, a group hug or something.
>> Okay, good, thanks.
>> Oh.
We just had a really good talk.
>> That's what I wanted, yeah.
>> That's not what you wanted.
>> That's not what I wanted,
but...
>> Right.
And so you...
>> Well opening that up to them
to...
>> Yeah.
Thank you.
>> No problem.
Things were looking pretty bad,
and I still think they're
looking pretty bad.
I don't want to give up.
I don't want to admit defeat,
but it's so hard to keep going.
We'll also have to see what Ozzy
has to say when he comes back
from Exile.
I definitely want to talk to
Ozzy about the future.
I definitely want to ask him
about how he feels with his
alliance and how he feels about
taking me with him.
>> How'd it go?
No way!
Are you serious?
>> Yeah.
>> I came back from Exile, and
as soon as I jump off the boat,
there was Erik looking like a
lost puppy dog.
He came right up to me and said,
"I know it's a long shot, but
I've got to tell you something
about Ami."
>> Ami was trying to do
something with me, Tracy, and
Chet.
And then it was down to Tracy
and me, she was trying to sway
either Cirie or Amanda to do
whatever.
>> So you're being totally
honest that Ami was...
>> Yes, yes.
>> Did Ami try and get me out?
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
>> I'm going to write down Ami
tonight.
I just want you to know that.
>> All right.
>> And I would like you to help
me, as a fellow competitor, to
stay in this game.
>> Okay.
The way I play this game, as
soon as someone makes a move
against me, that's it.
I'm going to do whatever I can
to get them out as fast as I
can.
And that's what Ami did.
Erik, on the other hand, given
the opportunity, I think he will
prove trustworthy, and I'm
willing to take that chance and
that risk.
>> And that makes sense, but...
but I still think that Ami...
>> We can't trust Ami at all.
>> No?
>> No.
>> Well...
>> You know what I found out
from Erik?
Ami was trying to get me out.
Ami's a lying little snot.
>> Who can we trust more,
though?
>> Erik.
>> I don't think so.
>> You think Ami?
>> At least we know what Ami is
capable of and what she's here
to... how she's here to play.
Erik is more dangerous than he
appears.
>> So is Ami.
>> I don't know.
>> PROBST: Four times in a row.
Cirie, you're clearly the
inferior tribe at this point.
>> It's horrible.
We just can't figure out why we
keep losing.
And it sucks around camp for
morale for us.
>> PROBST: Erik, interesting
situation you're in right now,
because the last three people
voted off have been fans.
There's only one fan left.
>> I know.
I understand that the fans have
been going, one after another,
and I understand that I could be
the one tonight.
I mean, I feel hopeless.
A week ago, I was happy, and to
have it go this way, it baffles
me.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, looks to me
like it's favorites versus fans
still, in a lot of ways.
>> Yeah, alliances were made to
people that you feel the most
trust, and that's how we came to
be a tribe in the beginning, the
favorites.
But all of a sudden, the game
gets in the way, and the
favorites that might feel
they're at the bottom of the
pecking order start playing the
fans, start playing both sides
of the spectrum, and that's when
it starts getting a little bit
funky.
And now I'm starting to realize
that certain things are not what
they seem.
>> PROBST: Ami, you're tearing
up.
>> Well, I obviously know Ozzy
is talking about me right now.
>> Why would you think that?
>> Because I know Erik has been
all day long saying how I've
been playing both sides and all
of that.
>> To be honest, the day that
the fans arrived, Ami said, "I
need some help.
You guys are numbers."
>> Yeah, I could have gone with
those guys the first vote--
could have.
It would have been easy.
We had the numbers to do it.
And I didn't.
It's just now that finally I
feel like I'm part of the tribe,
you're telling me that,
"Whatever, I don't trust her, I
don't believe her."
>> How have we ever made you
feel like you're not part of the
tribe?
We've always been together.
We've always had the plan to try
and keep us as strong as
possible as...
>> But I haven't always felt
like I'm part of the tribe.
You guys go off, and you make
decisions that you don't ask me
about.
>> When?
>> Like when you guys were
making decisions for the first
few times with everybody else,
it didn't include me.
You guys made the decisions.
>> I just want to know were you
gunning for me with Tracy and
Erik, or were you not?
>> There is no way I would have
ever voted for you with Tracy
and Erik, ever.
I was giving them hope and
letting them have a good,
peaceful camp, and there is no
way I would have ever voted for
you, ever, Ozzy.
The only way I would vote for
you is to win the million
dollars, period.
>> PROBST: Cirie, take me
through the dilemma.
It's easy to keep with what
you've been doing and get rid of
the next fan, and we've still
got four favorites together.
Now Ami's in question.
How do you make a decision on
which way to go?-- because it's
a huge vote.
>> I think all the favorites
have a mutual respect for each
other, and you know, it's like
the home team.
You don't want the visitors to
come in and win the game.
( sighing )
I think you just have to go with
your gut feeling, what you'll
believe and what you're not
going to believe.
>> PROBST: Amanda, take me
through the part of you that
wants to believe Ami.
Maybe Ami is telling the truth.
>> I think Ami is, honestly,
like, a really good person.
We've gotten close.
We've been a tribe for 20-some
days now, and I want to believe
what she's saying.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, give me your
take on what's happening here.
>> God, I really want to trust
Ami.
I really do.
And I feel like I have, for the
most part, for the whole, entire
game.
>> It just kills me that he says
he wants to.
I can't believe that he doesn't.
>> PROBST: Clearly, tonight's
vote is about one simple
quality: trust.
Erik, why should they believe
your story?
>> I have no other option.
I feel that I'm backed up
against the wall, and I said,
"You know what?
The truth is fine."
And I have to tell it in hopes
that they would see that and
say, "Yeah, Ami is not
trustworthy," or, "Ami is a
threat to the tribe well-being
and to us, as individuals, after
the merge."
That's all I have.
That's all I have to give was
that.
>> PROBST: Ami, why should this
tribe believe your story?
>> I'm going to set aside all
the past of where I've voted and
what I've done and all that.
They know where I'm coming from.
The biggest thing is is my heart
is in this.
I want to fight for this tribe.
I want to stick together.
I don't want to go out now.
We have so much more that we can
conquer together.
I want to fight as hard as I can
in every challenge.
I've looked you in the eyes, and
you know you can trust me.
I know you know it.
I know you know it without
words.
And I know you do too.
Erik is a really good guy.
He's doing the best he can.
I have everything invested in
this.
I want to keep Parvati in.
I want to keep James in.
I even want to keep Eliza in.
I want to be here.
I swear I'll give you everything
I have.
>> PROBST: It's time to get to
the vote.
Ozzy has immunity for tonight's
tribal council only because he
did not participate in the
challenge.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
>> I don't even know what to
say, Erik.
You're a good guy.
>> Ami, you're an awesome,
awesome woman.
I'm sorry it had to come to
this.
What can I say?
This game's hell.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the tribal council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Ami.
Erik.
One vote Ami, one vote Erik.
Ami.
Two votes Ami, one vote Erik.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites,
Ami.
That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> You guys better start
winning.
>> PROBST: Ami, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good luck, you guys.
>> PROBST: Well, tonight's vote
seems to speak to the idea that
sometimes you've got to listen
to your gut and act on it.
Clearly, that is what you guys
did tonight.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> You are merged!
>> We merged!
>> I'm ready to go beyond fans
versus favorites.
>> Alexis has to go.
>> I think a bit of jealousy is
coming into play.
>> Oh, my God!
It's not the idol.
>> It is the idol.
>> It's not the idol.
>> Why do you say that?
>> Because that can't be the
idol.
>> Why not?
>> Because it's just a stick.
>> It kills me that Ozzy and
Amanda didn't trust me, that I'm
not still there playing with
them.
The one day I finally feel like
I'm part of something, it's the
day I get voted out.
This game definitely plays
tricks on you.
You learn a lot about yourself.
Like, I really need to keep my
head up.
I really need to stay strong.
I'm blessed that I got to play
this game twice.