>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, Ozzy was in the best
position to make it to the final
four.
He was in an alliance with the
five remaining favorites.
>> I trust them, and you've got
to be able to trust some people
in this game.
>> PROBST: And he had the hidden
immunity idol.
His only competition seemed to
be Jason, who beat him in the
first individual immunity
challenge.
Nice work.
At the second individual
immunity challenge, it was down
to Jason and Parvati when food
was offered to the entire tribe
if one of them dropped out.
>> Jason!
You can make friends!
>> I won't vote you out.
>> PROBST: Then everyone in the
tribe promised Jason they would
spare him if he stepped down.
>> I'll guarantee.
>> PROBST: Jason took the deal,
giving up a chance at individual
immunity in order to improve his
position within the tribe.
>> Bon appétit.
>> PROBST: The favorites agreed
to vote Jason out anyway.
>> We'd have to be idiots not to
vote him out tonight.
>> PROBST: But Parvati decided
to double-cross Ozzy instead.
>> I'm going to have to be
untrustworthy and disloyal no
matter what.
>> PROBST: She recruited
everyone but James, Amanda, and
Erik and took Ozzy completely by
surprise.
Tenth person voted out of
Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites
and the second member of our
jury, Ozzy.
Ozzy, the tribe has spoken.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I understand why it happened.
But when you think about it,
like, a blindside, it only works
if it's airtight.
>> Right.
>> And obviously, like, I felt
obligated to Ozzy, so I would
have told him.
I probably would have told him,
and I think you guys did the
right decision for... to pull
that off.
I don't know where Amanda is
right now.
She totally, like, took off
somewhere.
>> Yeah.
>> And she's probably bumming
like crazy.
>> It's just another game.
>> Sometimes you got to pull the
punches.
>> Yeah.
>> They got it.
It's funny.
I like it.
It was a good move by everybody.
>> I'm very upset about what
happened last night.
What nerve for Cirie and Parvati
to go behind my back and vote
out Ozzy, making me look like an
idiot and the rest of my
alliance looking like idiots
because we voted for Jason.
You know, it's like Parv and
Cirie and Alexis and Natalie are
an alliance now, and I think
they want the men out of here.
I thought we were fine up until
those votes, and then another
Ozzy came up, and I was like,
"What the hell?"
Every single person here wanted
to vote for Jason.
It definitely told me that
they're here to play this game.
Game on.
Bring it on.
Like, let's do this.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> So hot.
>> I know.
If you give me one, I can add
one from over this side.
It's not so hot.
What is that, meat on your
finger hanging off like that?
>> Yeah.
I'm trying to put coconut juice,
coconut oil.
>> Oh, oh.
James's finger wasn't really
doing too good.
He's had this cut on it for a
few days now.
It was kind of swollen and kind
of infected.
You cannot just assume, "Oh,
this little cut, it's okay.
So what, we're living in a damp,
nasty cave with rats and bats
around us every 15 minutes.
No, this'll be fine."
>> I just did three loops around
the island looking for your ass.
>> Who are you talking to?
>> You.
Where were you?
Oh, my God!
I need to do some serious damage
control today.
James and Amanda are pissed at
me, furious for voting Oz out.
But I made my bed.
I have to lie in it.
I knew as soon as I made this
move, things were going to get
crazy.
>> Where are you going with
this?
>> Where am I going with what?
>> The paranoia got to you and
you just made a big move.
>> What?
>> I mean, you'll be all right.
>> I couldn't win against Ozzy.
I would be a fool to have kept
him in the game.
>> What is your plan?
Who are you taking with you?
I'm just curious to know.
>> To three?
>> Yeah.
>> Girls.
>> Yeah, I figured that.
>> I just wanted to say sorry
because I couldn't tell you.
>> No, sorry's not what you
mean.
Ha-ha's what you mean.
>> Well, I wanted to talk to
you, because I like you.
I didn't want it to be, like,
completely awkward.
>> Oh, it's going to be awkward.
It's just funny.
There's always one that always
got to eat the apple, can't just
leave the apple alone and just
enjoy the heavens.
No, you got to chew on that
apple.
>> Yeah, hopefully, because you
wouldn't give me credit for
having a plan anyways.
>> Why would I think that?
>> Because that's pretty much
how you've been acting towards
me this whole time.
>> That's a lie.
>> That I'm stupid.
>> No, I didn't say you were
stupid.
I said you were selfish, not
I mean, you can lie to me, you
can fool me, you can deceive
don't.
Don't insult your intelligence.
Don't try to act like you're
going to pull the wool over my
eyes with self-pity.
Just don't come up here trying
to give me a bunch of bluff.
>> I just wanted to talk to you,
honestly.
>> Huh?
>> I just wanted to talk to you.
>> And you have.
By her pulling that just showed
me who she really is.
Do I put up with people like
that?
No.
That's what kind of person she
is, and that's who we're dealing
with, and I just can't stand it.
>> I feel really bad that I
couldn't tell you last night.
I know, like, you feel really
out of the loop, but, like,
you're not.
>> What is the plan?
>> I'm thinking...
>> Because obviously it's the
girls together, right?
>> I'm thinking final five
girls, you know?
>> I don't want Parvati to know
that I'm mad at her, because
Parvati is pretty much running
the show at this point.
She has Natalie and Alexis
wrapped around her finger, and
Cirie didn't even tell me that
she was voting for Ozzy.
So she's got little Cirie
wrapped around her finger.
You know, I just hope that we're
all still cool.
>> Yeah.
>> That's what I'm coming down
here for, because I can tell
you're not happy.
>> I understand.
Like, I really understand.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I hope you guys trust me.
>> No, no, we totally trust you.
It's just with Ozzy and not
wanting him... we knew you
probably didn't want him to go
just yet.
>> So is it still, like, us
three to the end?
>> I say yeah.
>> I don't see why not.
>> Okay, yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> You know I love you, "Legs."
Oh, I feel so bad for you.
You look so sad.
>> You know, I'd like to believe
them, but obviously, they have
other plans right now that I'm
not aware of, and it'd be stupid
of me to buy what they're
telling me right now.
This is where the game gets
interesting.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Always smiles at the Survivor
auction.
Welcome to the Survivor auction.
( applause )
>> Woo!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: You each received a
wallet with $500.
Today, you're going to use that
money to bid on items.
The bidding will be in $20
increments.
There is no sharing of money or
items.
>> Oh.
>> Ouch.
>> PROBST: Shall we get started?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First item.
>> I'll take 20.
>> 40.
>> 60.
>> PROBST: 60 to Parvati.
>> 80.
>> 100.
>> 120, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Going once, twice,
sold to Cirie.
Let me count this.
( laughter )
>> Oh, I forgot.
>> PROBST: Yeah, nice.
( laughter )
>> No, she didn't!
>> PROBST: You want to see what
$120 buy you?
>> I hope it's good.
>> Hot dog, French fries, and
all the fixings.
>> I'm so mad at you.
I can't even look at you.
>> Ooh, it smells good.
Ooh, it's a fat one!
>> PROBST: Next item, covered.
>> 20.
>> PROBST: 20 to Alexis.
>> 40.
>> PROBST: 40 to Erik.
>> 60.
>> PROBST: 60 to Alexis.
>> I'll say 80.
>> PROBST: $80 to Erik.
Going once, going twice, sold
for $80.
Hang tight.
Before you get up, Erik, you can
keep this or...
>> Window number two.
>> Oh.
>> Ah, it's another one!
>> PROBST: You can trade it for
this.
>> I'll trade it.
>> PROBST: You're going to trade
it.
>> Yeah, I'll trade it.
>> PROBST: All right.
Come on up.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Right here, 80 bucks.
>> 80.
>> PROBST: All right, Erik, this
is what you bought for 80 bucks.
You gave up octopus...
>> All right!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: ...for a huge tray of
nachos.
>> Oh, nachos!
>> That's good!
Damn, I want that one!
>> Oh, my God, there's
guacamole.
>> PROBST: Next item, going to
stay covered.
>> 240.
>> PROBST: Sold to Natalie.
>> It'd better be good.
Please, let it be good.
>> PROBST: Fruit bat soup.
>> Ah.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Not even interested.
>> I'll eat it.
>> PROBST: You want it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: James, all yours.
Take a bite of that for me.
>> You got to take the skin off
first.
That's the secret.
You get past the skin, you're
all right.
>> PROBST: Free food.
Peanut butter jelly sandwich.
>> 20.
>> 40.
>> 60.
>> 80.
>> 140.
>> PROBST: That's to Amanda.
>> 160.
>> PROBST: That's 160 to Alexis.
>> 180.
>> 200.
>> PROBST: 200 to Alexis.
>> 220... 240.
>> PROBST: 240 to Amanda.
>> 260.
>> PROBST: 260 to Parvati.
>> 280.
>> PROBST: Wow, 280 to Amanda
for a peanut butter and jelly.
Sold!
It's amazing the value you put
on food when you don't have it.
All right, next item.
>> 100.
>> PROBST: 100 to Alexis.
>> Two.
>> PROBST: 200 to Natalie.
>> 220.
>> 240.
>> PROBST: 240 to Natalie.
Going once, twice, sold to
Natalie.
$240 bought you this.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: It's a bottle with a
note.
Open it and read it.
>> "You must choose one person
to go to Exile Island
immediately, and you take all of
the money they have left."
>> Damn!
>> I've been there twice.
I don't want to go back.
Please!
>> Well, is the idol replanted
since it wasn't ever played?
>> PROBST: Because Ozzy was
voted out while in possession of
the idol and he never played it,
that idol is dead.
A new idol has been hidden.
New clues await.
>> Um...
Jason.
>> Ah.
>> PROBST: Jason going to Exile
Island.
>> But this is also good for
Jason, if he gets the immunity
idol.
Like, I don't know why he's
tripping.
>> PROBST: That's true.
This time maybe you'll get a
real one.
All right, Jason, give your
money to Natalie.
You can head out the same way
you came in.
The boat's waiting for you.
>> Bye, Jason.
>> Bye, kid.
>> PROBST: Next item, this item
comes with another layer.
>> 20.
>> 40.
>> 60.
>> 80.
>> 100.
>> Stop playing, Parvati.
200.
>> 240.
>> PROBST: 240 to Parvati.
>> Three.
>> 320.
>> 340.
>> 360.
>> 380.
>> PROBST: 380 to Natalie.
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Going once, twice,
sold to Natalie.
Looks like Jason's cash just
came in very handy.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: A gigantic chocolate
cake for Natalie.
Now, I said this item has
another layer to it.
>> What the hell is that?
>> PROBST: It's a note.
Turn around and read it to the
group.
>> Oh, not that again.
>> Okay.
"You must share this cake with
three of your tribe mates.
You have 60 seconds to eat as
much as you can."
Parvati and Alexis and Cirie.
Okay.
Seriously, don't hog the cake.
I haven't had any food.
>> No way.
>> I'm a little aggro right now,
okay?
>> PROBST: All right, you three
stay there.
You get the first taste.
>> Oh, my God.
Do it right, mama!
Yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, guys, come
get this.
Sit down.
I'll tell you when your 60
seconds starts.
Don't eat yet.
Go back over there.
You guys ready?
60 seconds starts now.
Go.
>> Go!
>> Mm!
>> I'll give them 20 bucks each
to lick their fingers when
they're done.
>> Mm!
>> PROBST: You have 15 seconds
left.
You better start shoving cake
down.
Whatever is in your mouth you
can finish.
Everything else you've got to
drop.
Five seconds, four, three, two,
one, and you're done.
>> Oh!
>> Awesome!
>> That's just too much
chocolate.
I'm sorry.
>> Erik?
>> Yeah.
>> How much did you say you were
going to pay?
>> I'd say 20 bucks to lick your
fingers.
>> 20 a finger?
>> All right, how about 40 bucks
to lick your fingers?
>> He's serious!
>> Okay, uh-huh.
>> Oh, baby.
>> "Oh, baby."
>> Oh, that's sad.
>> Mm, mm, mm.
>> Something's wrong with that
boy.
He really has problems, poor
thing.
>> PROBST: The Survivor auction
is over.
>> Like, I should not have sent
him, but I didn't think anybody
else wanted to miss out.
>> I'd have gone.
>> I was looking at everybody,
and nobody was giving me an
answer.
>> I know.
>> If he gets that idol, I'm
going to lose it.
I'm going to lose it.
>> Y'all shouldn't be worried
unless he's, like, really good
with clues and puzzles.
>> Jason's on Exile.
We all want him gone.
The little bitch now has two
days of sunshine with the
immunity idol.
Guaranteed, hands down, bitch
will find it, and that bitch
being Jason.
>> Hey, I'm not kidding.
I say we check his bag when he
gets back-- like, immediately,
because it'll come just in his
pants.
>> Definitely, like, the second
we see him.
>> Yes!
He has been on the biggest lucky
streak I have ever seen of
anyone.
If there was a lottery right
now, he'd be winning it.
>> Well, it'd better rain.
Like, if I want rain at all,
it's tonight.
>> Seriously.
>> "To find the idol that you
seek, go north to a familiar
location.
You must step up but look for
cracks to find your
destination."
Well, doesn't seem too hard.
Go down there.
If my time out here goes similar
to my last time out here finding
the fake hidden immunity idol,
you know, I should find it in a
breeze.
Number two.
So far, the game has thrown me
so many curves balls.
But since stepping down from the
last immunity challenge, I think
things have definitely changed
for me out here.
I was a little bummed right away
when Natalie chose me, but
hopefully Natalie sent me out to
Exile Island so that I could
find it in the event that
Natalie and I might work
together in using the hidden
immunity idol.
Okay, back across the waterway
there.
I believe that I can trust
Natalie in the fact that, one,
she kept her word to me at last
tribal council when we voted out
Ozzy, and it's in her best
interest to keep me along in
this game.
There you go.
Oh!
Yes!
I feel pretty stupid falling for
the fact that Ozzy made me a
fake idol.
This is not the fake hidden
immunity idol, and the decision
of Natalie to send me to Exile
Island was a strategic move on
her part.
I feel like for the first time
in the game, I'm actually part
of a successful alliance.
Right now I feel the most
comfortable I've felt in the
entire game.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, we have to act as
if Jason has the idol.
>> Yeah.
>> We need to have a plan.
>> As far as the idol goes,
like, I don't want anything
bouncing off and getting one of
us.
>> I mean, if Jason doesn't win
tomorrow, cool, as planned.
>> Right, but just in case he
has the idol, we still have to
split the vote.
>> Even if we can convince him
that someone else needs to win
this challenge besides him,
let's do it.
Like, whatever we need to do.
>> Yeah.
>> We have to get into his head,
or else I don't think he's going
to lose.
>> Yeah, I agree.
I think we can get in his head.
>> He won't buy anything I say
to him, so...
>> Nat can say it.
I know he'll believe Nat.
>> We've concocted a beautiful
plan to disarm Jason's lack of
trust, make him feel
comfortable, make him feel
comfortable enough.
So we want to blindside him with
not using his immunity and
allowing one of us to win;
therefore, he doesn't win, and
he's out.
Worst-case scenario, he has to
play his idol, and he stays, but
at least his idol's up and out.
You know, before the next
immunity, as soon as I see
Jason, be like, "Dude, I saved
your ass once.
I basically gave you the
immunity idol.
You owe me."
>> That's all you have to say.
>> I just think that it's
similar to Ozzy in the sense
that we have one chance to
blindside him.
>> Yeah.
>> At this point, Jason would be
an idiot not to believe anything
I say.
He thinks that I'm warming up to
him, which I am absolutely not.
If this goes, I mean, this will
just be brilliant, because not
only will it happen... have
happened once with Ozzy; it'll
happen twice, back to back,
girls against the guys.
( laughter )
>> That's, like, freaking...
>> Genius!
>> ...genius.
>> Hell hath no furry.
>> "Deja vu, this may feel
familiar.
Don't panic, but still you'd
better hurry.
If you haven't learned from the
past, you may be the next to
join the jury."
Hmm.
>> Got to win.
It's day 30.
It's my 22nd birthday, and I
really think I need to compete
well this time.
If Jason wins immunity today, I
have a feeling that it's either
me or James on the chopping
block for tribal council, simply
because the women are very
strong right now.
I really need to get ferocious
on this.
I really need to try my best,
because I feel like I could be
gone on my birthday, and that
would be terrible.
Big, green birthday present.
>> Happy birthday.
>> I wish we had stuff we could
give you.
>> I know.
I do too.
>> He's like, "Tell me about
it."
>> Hey, babe.
>> This challenge is vital in
all the other steps leading up
to the end of this game for the
girls.
>> What else is in there, Nat,
anything?
>> No key, I hope.
>> A key and a chain.
>> Oh, no.
>> A lock and chain.
I don't want to do any diving.
>> If all goes to plan, Jason
will feel comfortable enough not
to play his idol and he will not
win immunity today.
So he's done.
Worst-case scenario, James goes
home tonight in lieu of Jason,
if we can't get Jason.
So it's either James or Jason
tonight.
And as evil as women can be and
diabolical and cutthroat and go
for the jugular as women are and
just suck blood, we do want Erik
to have a good birthday on day
30.
Today's his birthday.
He's 22.
So he's not going home today.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Jason,
returning from Exile Island.
>> How was the line?
Be honest.
>> Welcome back.
>> Hi, guys.
>> Howdy.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Parvati, take back the necklace.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, all eight
of you will race to throw rocks
at tiles.
When you break your tile, you'll
drop a bundle of puzzle pieces.
The first four to break their
tile move on to the next round,
where you will dig for a key to
unlock the puzzle pieces.
You'll then assemble the wheel,
place it onto a winch, then spin
the wheel to lower a set of two
planks.
The first two to lower their
planks move on to the final
round, where you will use those
planks to cross a rope bridge.
You'll then make your way across
a series of discs and to the
finish platform.
First person to the platform
wins immunity, is guaranteed at
least one more day in this game.
Losers, tribal council, somebody
going home.
Draw for spots.
We'll get started.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
This is for immunity.
The first four people to break
their tile move on to the next
round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Yellow's in.
Jason's moving on.
Erik's moving on.
James is moving on.
We're looking for one more
person, and it is Amanda.
Amanda, James, Erik, and Jason
moving on to the next round.
Here we go.
The first two to lower their
planks and cross the black line
move on to the final.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You're looking for a key, one
key.
James has his key.
Erik has his key.
James and Erik both have their
keys.
Got to unwrap them, then unlock
those puzzle pieces.
Jason's found his key.
He's working on it.
James has his lock undone.
Amanda is still digging.
>> Hey, where is it?
>> PROBST: Erik has his lock
open.
James working on the puzzle, has
it together quickly.
Erik working on his puzzle.
James and Erik both lowering
their planks.
Two people are moving on.
Amanda still digging for that
key.
Jason trying to get his puzzle
together, quickly falling out of
it.
Got to hit the table.
James, you're good!
James unclips.
James moving on.
Erik, you're good.
Erik unclips and moving on.
James and Erik moving on to the
final.
Here we go.
It is James and Erik for
immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Got to make your way across
using your planks.
Very different strategies.
James trying to go sideways,
trying to keep his balance, and
it doesn't work.
James is in.
Got to go back to the start.
>> Don't knock Erik over.
You're going to knock him over.
>> PROBST: James loses his
plank, got to get back, losing a
lot of time.
James tried a strategy that did
not work.
Erik doing something similar,
going from the side, but he's
using his knees.
James trying a new strategy,
struggling to hang on.
Erik not panicking at all,
taking his time, keeping that
lead.
Immunity and a one-in-seven shot
for the winner of this
challenge.
Erik doing a good job of going
slow and easy.
James is in the role of having
to move quickly, try and make up
ground, take some risks.
He's gaining on Erik.
Erik now going back to riskier
moves.
Instead of one plank at a time,
he's skipping.
James making up some ground
again.
>> ...the rest of the way.
>> PROBST: James is back in it.
>> Oh, oh, oh, oh.
>> PROBST: Erik getting very
close.
Erik to the platform.
Now he's got to make his way
across the discs.
James to the platform.
James has got to get across the
discs.
First to the pole.
Erik wins immunity!
( applause )
>> Damn.
>> Happy birthday!
>> Woo!
>> PROBST: Erik, come on up.
>> Nice job, Erik.
>> PROBST: A round of applause.
Congratulations.
Erik safe tonight at tribal
council.
For the rest of you, somebody is
going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at tribal.
>> Birthday boy.
Hey, Erik, it's your birthday.
One out of eight.
I keep telling you.
You won on your birthday.
>> I was telling them, what are
the odds, honestly?
>> That's awesome.
I'm proud of you.
That was a tough one too.
>> I thought so.
>> I'm going to get a puff ball
or two, maybe bring it into the
cave.
( Parvati squealing )
>> So far, part A of the plan is
perfect.
>> I looked over at Parvati, and
we were like, "Run, Erik!"
>> I was so nervous.
I was hyperventilating.
I was like...
>> When Erik made it, I jumped
up like... I didn't scream,
though.
>> So the fact that it came down
to Erik and James in the end,
and we needed Erik to win in
order for the plan to work out,
and then Erik did win, I was
ecstatic.
I think all the girls were
jumping up and down and
screaming silently inside their
heads.
>> The plan is in play.
( laughter )
It's like the black widow
brigade.
Like, all the girls are coming
together, and we're spinning the
guys around as much as we can,
just spinning them and spinning
them, until they don't know
which way is up, and then we're
devouring them one at a time.
>> Are you going to go look
for... what are you going to go
do?
>> Yeah, I'm going to go look
for crab too, in a little bit.
>> It's raining.
They're not out when it rains.
>> And bring back some salt
water.
>> You want to take that bucket?
Or you're going to take the pot.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> I'll look in the nets too.
>> He didn't go anywhere but
right here, right?
>> He went down there.
>> I mean, he came straight up
here.
Where is his stuff at?
I don't know.
Where's the bag?
Oh, the bag is over there too.
Hurry up, Nat.
>> It's in here.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Grab it.
>> It's it.
>> That's the stuff.
>> I knew he had it.
Because he was like, "I know you
sent me for strategy purposes."
>> He won't play it tonight.
He won't play it tonight.
>> I told him I would go into
everything a little bit later.
But I'm like, "This is done."
He's like, "Oh."
He's like, "You sent me for a
reason, huh?"
I was like, "Yeah."
I was able to have a
conversation with Jason at the
challenge, literally 30 seconds,
hopefully got my point across in
one swift motion.
So I think we're good.
It would be perfect, it would be
brilliant for Jason to go out
just like Ozzy-- blindsided, no
idea that it's... what's hitting
him in the face.
I'd love it.
>> And, yeah, we can use it
however... because I wanted to
say to you personally, I didn't
get a chance to yesterday, you
know, but thank you for keeping
your word, and it means a lot to
me, and you have mine in this
game from now on, so...
>> Cool, cool, thank you.
So yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, the thing is... here's
the thing.
James is going home tonight.
>> Is that what you're thinking?
>> Uh-huh.
>> That'd be great.
And yeah, to let you know, I did
find it.
And... yeah, like that.
( snaps fingers )
>> Yeah.
Did you see me ask Jeff.
I was like, "So is the immunity
idol back out?"
>> Uh-huh.
>> And he was like, "Oh, by the
way, da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da."
And you were like this, and I'm
like, "And... Jason."
>> I know, I know.
But it was smart.
It was very smart of you to send
me.
I'm hoping that Natalie is
telling the truth, that we're
voting for James tonight.
She kept her word to me at last
tribal council, when we voted
out Ozzy, and you know, I'm
going to have to trust her this
tribal council as well.
After what you guys did for me
last time, my word is as good as
your word, which, you know, so
far in this game, has been good,
so...
>> You know, I think I'm pretty
evil.
I think I could be pretty evil.
What I am now is I'm definitely
in "I will get you" mode.
I'm in game mode.
And now I'm actually having a
lot more fun.
I'm getting to be more of
myself, which is proving to be
pretty ruthless and pretty
stone-cold bitch and pretty
cutthroat.
And I have a smile on my face.
Sorry about that.
>> I have, like, searched every
avenue.
I'm telling you, I don't know
what to do.
I honestly have no idea.
You know what?
If it's not him, I mean, they're
writing your name down.
>> Who is?
>> You are?
>> Yeah.
Because I'm saying maybe you
could too, but... you think?
>> That'd be awesome.
>> Yeah.
I wouldn't mind.
>> I get really, unbelievably
fourth grade uncomfortable when,
like, any guy even remotely
makes a move.
Like, I'm not the cool girl at
all.
>> Really?
>> Really, really.
>> See, I'm like a man eater
now.
I'm like, "You..."
>> Man eater!
( laughter )
>> I'd love to blindside Jason,
because it would be 2-0, the
ladies, just at the jugular,
flossing my teeth with his
jugular.
Either way, it's a win-win.
Either Jason goes home, or Jason
stays and unearths the idol, or
it's James going home.
Either way, it's still the five
girls down to two guys.
Picking them off...
one by one.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury.
So last tribal council, you not
only vote out one of the
strongest physical threats in
this game, but you vote out one
of the biggest providers.
Parvati, does this group feel
like we don't really need
providers anymore?
>> I think we've all felt kind
of okay on our own as far as
providing for ourselves for a
while.
Like, every person is kind of
providing.
>> PROBST: James, seeing that
they don't need providers
anymore, another big physical
threat in this game is you.
>> Yeah, it don't look that good
for James right now.
The social butterflies have done
their work, and yeah, I'm
definitely on the chopping
block.
>> PROBST: How frustrating would
it be to be voted out tonight,
James, after everything you've
done in terms of keeping this
tribe afloat?
>> It was all about trying not
to make certain people eat that
apple.
You know, and if somebody want
to be greedy-- Parvati, she want
to make herself in a better
position, so she did what she
had to do.
She got rid of Ozzy.
And now I'm pretty much next,
you know, and it's very
frustrating.
I mean, I could try to politic,
but I really suck at that.
So, I mean, what can you do?
>> PROBST: Erik, looking at
physical threats, obviously,
you're a physical threat.
It's got to feel great to have
immunity.
>> I couldn't agree more with
that.
I mean, I felt like I was in the
same position as James: if I
didn't win, then I was going
home.
And if everybody feels like they
can provide for themselves,
that's one more reason why you
don't need Erik around.
>> PROBST: The other significant
thing about the last vote is
that you're still here, Jason.
Has your social standing in this
game truly changed as a result
of stepping down off that
immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
Every little difference I make
around camp is changing my
social standing in this game.
But I was sent away to Exile,
where I was gone for two days.
So you know, it's difficult to
say where I stand in the tribe
right now.
>> PROBST: You say you're not
sure because you were sent to
Exile Island.
Two sides to that coin.
It could be a sentence to go
there.
It could be an opportunity.
>> It was an opportunity for me
to look for the idol, but at
this point in the game, I wanted
to stay with my tribe mates and
really, you know, show them that
I can make these differences.
So you know, I'll have to see
how it plays out.
>> PROBST: Natalie, is it
possible to change your standing
in the game that quickly?
>> Absolutely.
It's constantly changing,
constantly.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Erik, you have the immunity
necklace, unless you want to do
something crazy and give it to
somebody else.
>> I'm not crazy.
I think I'm going to keep it.
>> PROBST: Erik is safe tonight.
You cannot vote for Erik.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Amanda you're up.
>> James, you played a good
game.
Unfortunately, Parvati got you
in the end.
>> You couldn't just frolic
naked and enjoy the heavens.
You had to eat the damn apple.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol, and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, James.
Jason.
One vote James, one vote Jason.
James.
Two votes James, one vote Jason.
Parvati.
Two votes James, one vote Jason,
one vote Parvati.
James.
That's three votes James, one
vote Jason, one vote Parvati.
Jason.
That's two votes Jason, three
votes James, one vote Parvati.
Jason.
That's three votes Jason, three
votes James, one vote Parvati.
One vote left.
11th person voted out of
Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites
and the third member of our
jury, Jason.
That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Jason, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Well, after back-to-back
blindsides, anybody who still
feels safe is a fool.
James, on your way out, I want
medical to look at your finger.
Everybody else, grab your
torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> I work with my hands, so it's
very important I get this thing
fixed as soon as possible.
>> PROBST: A new idol has been
hidden.
The first clue awaits you at
Exile Island.
>> That's Jeff Probst!
He's just standing there!
>> I was definitely played today
by Natalie and the rest of the
girls.
They did the same thing in
voting out Ozzy.
I should have been a little more
wary of what they were telling
me.
What they did tonight will
definitely come back to haunt
them as I'm sitting up there on
the jury.
I just wish I would have been a
little smarter and played the
hidden immunity idol when I had
the chance.