>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor:
Erik was the last man left in
the game.
And the women's alliance
desperately wanted him out.
>> It's us and Erik.
>> We need to figure out what we
need to do.
>> JEFF: But when he won the
immunity challenge, Erik threw a
wrench into their plans.
>> What are we all thinking?
>> I couldn't win against
Amanda.
>> JEFF: So Natalie, Alexis, and
Erik decided to vote out Amanda.
>> ♪ Da, da, da, da. ♪
>> JEFF: Cirie was still tight
with Amanda and Parvati, but
reluctant to force a tie.
>> So what do I do, make it a
tie?
>> You know that I would.
>> JEFF: At tribal council,
Amanda tore into Erik for
turning his back on her.
>> I helped you stay here
through the merge, and then I
was asking for your help, and
you clearly denied me of that.
>> JEFF: Then Amanda pulled off
the biggest blindside yet by
playing the hidden immunity
idol.
>> ♪ But I got it. ♪
>> JEFF: The rest of the tribe
was stunned as Alexis was sent
home.
Alexis, the tribe has spoken.
Only five are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I didn't have it when I told
you guys I didn't have it.
I got it afterwards.
>> Whoo-ee, tribal council, boy,
is getting dangerous, from the
idols floating around and people
using them and not using them.
You want me to make a fire?
>> Can do you it in the dark?
>> I mean, Amanda put me through
the wringer.
She is good, though, because she
had me right at the brink of
being willing to make it a tie
vote.
You know, I guess that's what
she needed to see to know that
she can trust me.
>> It was a pretty wild night.
>> They took out Alexis.
That's... if Parvati and Cirie
are smart, they'll recognize
that Amanda is very popular with
the jury, and they won't take
her.
>> It just doesn't make sense
for anyone to take her to the
final three.
It doesn't make any sense.
>> Yeah.
I would like to see Amanda
just... outie.
At tribal council, Amanda made
me feel like a fool, and I
definitely am pissed off about
that.
But everything can be switched
up with the hidden immunity
idol.
I want us to find the hidden
immunity idol.
That's the problem with Exile
Island, though, because if they
win, they can send anybody.
And I don't know if they would
send me.
To go to Exile Island at this
point, you have to find that
idol, because it's the last
chance you get to use it.
So whoever gets the idol, that's
pretty much like winning
individual immunity.
And then if I win, like if I
win... I'm going to try and win.
Okay.
>> And if I win you want me to
send you?
I mean, that's in our best
interest right now.
>> I think so, yes.
You need to.
Probably... like, I don't want
to go, because it's Exile, but
we have to at this point.
At this point, I'm weighing the
pros and cons of different
choices I could make in this
game.
I might have to listen to
Natalie and go with Natalie.
But nothing is set in stone
right now.
I mean, everything is just...
it's still moving, it's still
kind of evolving.
So at this point I don't trust
anybody in this game.
I really can't 100% trust
anybody.
But I do have to pick sides.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Don't even qualify it.
He's going.
>> Exactly.
That's what I'm thinking.
I don't really have a question
mark about Cirie anymore.
I pretty much tested her trust
when... she was pretty much
ready to pick rocks, so I'm not
too worried about Cirie's
loyalty.
You know, I trust my girls
again.
I trust Parv and Cirie, and it's
us three to the end.
>> It matters if he wins...
>> I know.
We don't want Erik or Natalie
going to Exile, because if one
of them gets the hidden immunity
idol, it could be the end of the
game for me, Parvati, or Cirie.
>> Erik is whoever gets to him
first.
It Amanda could get in his head
that she forgives him...
>> Yeah.
>> ...he'll do whatever she
says.
>> You.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, talk to him.
Try to get him...
>> So, what are your thoughts
now about things going on?
>> I'm looking to whatever this
reward is.
And... I don't know.
I feel like I could win it, like
I want to win it, because I am
starving.
I feel like it's going to be
food.
>> Amanda is a very, very
strategic player.
So I don't know if I can trust
her after she ripped me over the
coals at the last tribal
council.
And now she is pushing for
herself to go with me on the
reward.
>> I'm not going out of this
game without a fight.
>> Right.
>> And I think it's better that
we team up, you being the most
physical player on the team and
me the most strategic and battle
against the odds rather than...
>> Than play into what they're
doing.
>> ...possibly lose a challenge
and be out.
>> That's how I do feel.
I feel very stressed.
>> You think?
Me, too.
>> It's true.
>> Erik's very, very naive, so I
think I can definitely
manipulate his mind into sending
Parvati to Exile.
>> What are your thoughts on
Exile today?
Natalie was pushing for me to
possibly go.
Like, she wanted me to go.
>> Of course she wants you to.
>> And I don't want to go at
all.
>> Because she wants you to be
weaker for the next challenge.
>> I don't want to go there at
all.
>> You're playing a physical
game.
Why would you weaken yourself?
>> That's true.
>> It doesn't make any sense.
>> True.
>> Why not send Parvati?
Parvati is so weak right now,
she won't even want to look for
it.
She'll just sit there on the
island.
>> It's really weird, because I
feel like I have some kind of
choice to make on the fact that
I'm starting to win some
challenges, and now I feel like
it's basically Natalie and
Amanda who are trying to talk me
into some different plan.
So it's very... who do you
trust?
Who do you really trust here?
>> You're good at thinking,
Erik.
Like, you're almost there
sometimes.
>> Almost there.
I mean, it's not all hair up on
my head.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
>> Sweet.
>> You guys ready to get to your
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Today's challenge is
going to test how well you know
this game you love so well.
For today's challenge, I'm going
to ask you questions about
favorite moments from past
seasons of Survivor.
Every time you get one right,
you score a point.
First to four wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: The winner of this
challenge will board a
helicopter.
You will take a beautiful flight
over the rock islands.
You will land at a luxury
resort.
>> Oh, my god!
>> JEFF: Massage, meal.
>> Meal!
>> JEFF: You'll return to camp
in the morning.
In addition, the winner of the
challenge will send one person
to Exile Island.
Because Amanda played the hidden
immunity idol at the last tribal
council, there is yet another
hidden immunity idol.
The last time you can use the
hidden immunity idol is the next
tribal council.
That means you have one chance
to find the idol, one time to
play it.
Big enough stakes?
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: All right, we'll get
started.
All right, first question.
On which season of Survivor did
a castaway have a pet snake?
Everybody locked in?
Cirie makes a last-minute
change, and it's a good thing
she did.
The correct answer is Pearl
Islands.
Cirie gets it right.
Erik gets it right.
Rupert had a pet snake named
Balboa.
One point Cirie, one point Erik.
Next question.
In which season of Survivor did
a shark bite a survivor, and in
retaliation the survivor bit it
back?
If you are a fan of this game,
you should know this.
Erik says it was the first
season of Survivor.
That is not right.
Parvati and Cirie says Palau.
Palau is wrong.
Natalie and Amanda say Survivor
All-Stars.
All-Stars is right.
Amanda and Natalie both score a
point.
Richard Hatch got bitten by a
shark and he bit it back.
>> His teeth, right there, he's
got me.
>> JEFF: Cirie, Amanda, Natalie,
and Erik all with one.
Playing to four.
Next question:
In which season of Survivor did
a tribemate ask another
tribemate to pee on their hand
after being stung by a sea
urchin?
If you saw the season, you'll
remember this moment.
One person got it right.
The correct answer was Survivor:
Marcasis.
Erik, the only one to get it
right.
John asked Kathy to pee on his
hand after being stung by a sea
urchin.
>> I need somebody who can pee
on my hand.
Okay, okay.
>> JEFF: Erik moves into the
lead with two.
Cirie, Amanda, Natalie with one.
Parvati with zero.
Next question.
During which season of Survivor
was one of the castaways
evacuated after falling into the
fire?
Cirie, Parvati, and Erik all say
Survivor: Australia.
Erik is nodding, certain he's
right.
The correct answer is Survivor:
Australia.
Michael fell in the fire.
>> You're coming right now.
>> JEFF: That was 2001.
Erik was 14 years old.
Proof of your superfan status.
Erik now in the lead with three,
Cirie with two, Parvati, Amanda,
and Natalie with one.
Next question.
Erik, get this one right, you
win reward.
During which season of
Survivor did we first divide
the castaways into four separate
tribes?
When was the first time we
divided the castaways into four
separate tribes?
Parvati and Amanda both say the
Cooks.
Both wrong.
Cirie, Natalie, and Erik all
say Exile Island.
For the first time ever, you
have been divided into four
tribes by age and gender.
Exile island is correct.
Erik wins reward.
>> Survivor!
>> Spin it, baby.
>> JEFF: Nice job.
>> Thank you.
>> JEFF: Okay, first decision.
Who you sending to Exile Island?
Big strategy at this point.
>> I'm pretty sure that I want
to send Parvati to Exile Island.
>> Bye, guys.
>> JEFF: Parvati, boat's waiting
for you.
All right, Erik, next decision.
You have three people left.
You're going to choose one
person to go with you.
>> Before the challenge, I gave
Amanda my word that I would take
her.
And if she won, she had her word
that she would take me.
So I'm going to pick Amanda.
>> JEFF: Come on over, Amanda.
>> Thank you for keeping your
word.
>> JEFF: All right, Cirie,
Natalie, grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I got nothing for you.
>> Bye, guys.
>> JEFF: Erik, Amanda, nice
reward-- massage, nice meal,
good night's sleep.
>> Yes!
High five.
>> JEFF: Helicopter's waiting
for you.
Enjoy it.
Head on out.
>> Well, that was a doozy.
>> Mm-hmm.
I'm so upset.
Just stunned.
Like, if Erik seriously wanted
to get Amanda out, it would have
been a sure-fire thing to send
me to Exile, not Parvati.
Had a reward challenge.
Erik won.
I was hoping for him to win,
considering the conversation we
had this morning about it.
He said he'd send me to Exile or
take me on the reward.
Well, Parvati's on Exile, and he
chooses to take Amanda on the
reward, which adds up not one
iota.
>> Erik is a little weasel.
To me, where do his loyalties
lie if he told you he'd take
you, and he told her he'd take
her, and he took her, but she's
the one he's going to vote out?
I was kind of just yanking
Natalie around a little bit,
which is fun for me because it's
killing her.
She thinks she has Erik in her
pocket.
You do not feed and take care of
the person that you plan on
beating in the next immunity
challenge to make sure that
she's the one he's going to vote
out.
I mean, maybe that's a new
tactic that I don't know about.
>> Yeah.
>> "Let me make you as strong as
possible so I can vote you out."
The only pleasure I'm getting
out of today in not going on the
reward is seeing Natalie stress
out over Erik taking Amanda and
Parvati being on Exile.
>> Looks like a rat, smells like
a rat.
>> Give it cheese.
>> Yeah.
Is that them?
>> Where?
>> Natalie out there?
>> They're waving.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Yeah, they were.
>> Oh, look at this view!
>> Oh, my god!
>> This is awesome!
Woo!
>> Woo!
>> I'm really glad that you came
with me, that I chose you.
Honestly, I would want a friend
on this trip rather than a
stranger.
>> I feel the same way.
>> I know I didn't do what
Natalie wanted me to do.
If I brought Natalie, there
would be no relaxation, I don't
feel, and there was a part of me
that legitimately wanted to
spend time with Amanda and just
get to know her more as a friend
again.
>> Oh, my god!
>> I want to enjoy this as much
as I can.
And I feel like I'm thinking
about the game way too much,
and, thinking, "Is Amanda
manipulating you, are you
manipulating Amanda, whatever?"
And I don't want to think about
that at all.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Woo!
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my god.
>> This is the best reward ever.
>> Oh, yes.
>> Put them in.
>> Oh, my god.
We're getting foot treatments.
>> Whatever you're doing to the
toes...
I've never been to a spa in my
life.
>> Really?
>> Never been to a spa in my
life.
>> I feel like ever since I got
immunity last time, like, I'm,
like, the center of all that's
going on.
>> Well, you kind of are.
>> People are coming to me to
ask me, "What decision do you
want to make?"
And I'm just like, "I work in an
ice cream parlor.
I don't do this.
I don't make these decisions
about people."
>> Why not?
>> I just...
>> It's good to be in a power
position.
>> I'm just not used to it.
I'm going to kick myself
probably for whatever choices
that I made today, but I'm
trying to go with what I have.
I'm trying to go with what I can
see right now and make the best
decision.
I just need to step up, I think.
I mean, that's part of being a
man, being an ice cream man
instead of an ice cream boy.
>> I got here to Exile, and it's
gorgeous.
It's paradise for me.
This is kind of like my own
little private vacation.
I love it, because I really
needed this time to just chill,
maybe get a little tan, maybe
look for the idol if I want to.
If I don't want to, I don't have
to, because the reason for me
being here is just to prevent
Natalie and Erik from getting a
chance at getting the idol.
So it doesn't really matter if I
find the idol or not, because
Cirie, Amanda, and me, we have
the numbers.
>> I hate feeling bitter when
people come back from rewards.
But you just can't help it.
>> I'm not bitter about that.
I'm bitter about... well, we
promised each other if we won
we'd take each other.
What?
>> Where is everybody?
>> I don't know.
>> Probably sleeping.
>> Oh, yeah.
I think that's them.
>> Yeah.
>> Look who's back.
Bitches.
Don't try to look pitiful.
I know it was absolutely
wonderful.
I won that same challenge in my
season.
So I don't want to hear that it
wasn't fun and y'all didn't wake
up at 3:00 AM and eat more food.
>> We actually didn't eat more
food.
>> You should have.
That's what we did.
>> They had just dinner.
Like, you pick from the list.
>> We had, like, a waitress.
>> I wish we all could have
gone.
>> Returning to camp was very
bad.
I come back to camp, and Natalie
didn't even look at me.
She doesn't even talk to me.
It's no longer sunshine and
happiness.
I mean, she obviously had
resentment.
I know Nat is pissed off at me
for a lot of reasons.
>> Yeah.
I guess she thinks you should
have taken her, but she did...
see, I don't know.
Because she did say she wanted
to go to Exile.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And I guess she feels like if
you were going to vote Amanda
out, how would you take her on a
reward?
>> I feel regardless of what
happens right now, I'm going to
piss somebody off.
>> See, that's the thing.
>> I'm either going to piss off
Nat or piss off Amanda right now
for sure.
>> Do you think if Natalie was
sitting next to you she would
beat you hands down, or you
think if Amanda was sitting next
to you she'd beat you hands
down?
>> That's what I have to think
about.
>> That's the question.
>> I feel like me, you, and
Parvati are still on the fence,
because we don't know which one
is most likely to win all the
votes.
We think that both of them have
a really good chance.
So maybe me, you, and Parv
should go to the end and do that
instead.
>> That would mean we would get
rid of who?
>> Either Nat or Amanda.
>> God, this idiot.
I literally walked right in
front of Erik and heard his
entire conversation with Cirie
about how Natalie and Amanda are
the biggest jury vote threats.
Everybody's going to vote for
them on the jury so they can't
go to the final three.
You know what?
I could have literally bitch-
slapped him, smack him like his
mother.
>> What just happened just now?
>> I just overheard a complete
conversation.
>> He just told me that it would
probably be beneficial for me,
him, and Parv to go to the end.
>> I'm not surprised.
Am I surprised?
No, I know this is him.
See, the problem with Erik's
strategy is that there's five
people left, and four of them
are women.
And when you go to each woman
and you tell her something
different, pretty soon the women
are going to talk.
>> Idiot.
>> I might have screwed up quite
a bit.
I've been telling these girls
all these different things, and
I walked up on all three of them
talking to each other, and I'm
worried.
I'm definitely worried.
I feel like all of the women
here think I'm full of crap.
>> Don't you know everyone is
going to talk?
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Well, you need to pick one
side or the other.
You can't keep flipping.
You don't want to be with me
because you think I'm a threat.
And then you want to vote me
out.
And then all of a sudden, we're,
like, best friends.
And then I hear from everyone
else that you still are planning
on voting me out.
>> I make so many mistakes.
I know the girls don't trust me
at all.
And I'm scared I'm the next to
go.
I can't stress how important it
is that I win the next immunity.
Right now it's just like the
animal kingdom.
It's either you win and survive
or you fail and you die.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
I'll now bring in Parvati,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Hey, Parv.
>> JEFF: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
Erik, I'll take back the
necklace once again.
>> Here you go.
>> It's good to see you.
>> Hi, baby!
>> Hi!
>> Hey, girl.
>> JEFF: Once again, immunity is
back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
work to solve three puzzles.
Using a set of coordinates, you
will cross two ropes.
Where the ropes intersect,
you'll dig down to find a bag of
puzzle pieces.
Race back to your answer board,
solve the puzzle.
That puzzle will give you your
next set of coordinates, leading
you to another bag of puzzle
pieces.
The first person to solve all
three puzzles wins immunity, and
is guaranteed a spot in the
final four.
Losers, after 36 days, somebody
will be going home.
We'll draw for lanes, we'll get
started.
Here we go, for immunity and a
guaranteed spot in the final
four.
Survivors ready.
Go!
First plank will give you your
first set of coordinates.
You'll cross two ropes.
Where the ropes intersect,
you'll dig down to find a bag of
puzzle pieces.
That will give you your next set
of coordinates.
>> Sorry.
>> JEFF: Erik's crossed his
first two ropes.
He's digging for those puzzle
pieces.
Parvati starts digging.
Erik has his first bag, heading
back to solve his first puzzle.
Natalie is now digging.
Cirie now starts digging.
Amanda thinks she has it.
Now Amanda is digging.
Cirie comes back with her bag of
puzzle pieces.
Amanda has her first bag of
Erik has solved his first
puzzle, heading back out with
another set of coordinates.
Cirie has solved her first
puzzle.
Cirie now has her second set of
coordinates, heading back out.
Natalie has her first bag of
puzzle pieces.
>> Come on, baby!
>> JEFF: Erik has his second bag
of puzzle pieces.
Amanda now heading out with her
second set of coordinates.
Erik heading back to solve his
second puzzle.
Cirie has her two ropes in
place.
She's going to start digging,
hoping she remembered the right
symbols.
>> Turtle, white fish, bird,
seagull.
Turtle, white fish, bird,
>> JEFF: Erik solved his second
puzzle, heading out for that
third and final set of puzzle
pieces.
Natalie looking for that second
bag.
Erik with a big lead now.
Amanda, Cirie still digging.
Parvati nowhere close to being
in this challenge.
>> Oh, Jeff!
>> Bird, seagull.
Seagull.
Seagull, seagull, seagull.
>> JEFF: Erik lines up his
ropes, digging for that third
and final bag of puzzle pieces.
Natalie, Amanda, Cirie trying to
stay in this.
Erik has his third and final bag
of puzzle pieces!
Heading back to solve that final
puzzle.
Cirie, Amanda, and Natalie still
digging.
Parvati now heading out, looking
for that second set of
coordinates.
>> Oh, come on!
>> JEFF: Erik with a huge lead.
It is Erik's challenge to lose
at this point.
Guaranteed spot in the final
four if you win it.
Erik thinks he has it.
Guaranteed final four.
Erik wins immunity once again!
>> Damn.
>> JEFF: Once again, immunity is
yours.
And with this around your neck,
are you safe at tonight's tribal
council.
Erik is guaranteed a spot in the
final four.
Amanda, Natalie, Parvati, Cirie,
for one of you, your shot at the
million dollars will come to an
end tonight at tribal council.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> I just want you guys to tell
me.
>> Tell you what?
>> Just tell me if it's... if
it's me.
>> The way it's looking,
probably.
>> Yeah.
>> Yesterday, he worked us all
like cheap suits.
He told us all three same thing.
>> Wow.
>> Busted.
>> He got busted?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That sucks that he won!
God.
If he didn't have that necklace,
he'd be gone.
Probably not, huh?
>> What?
>> If he would give you his
necklace.
Do you think you could talk
him into giving you the
necklace?
>> Nat, work your magic.
You can convince him to give it
to you.
>> Why would it benefit him
giving me the necklace?
>> Say, "I'll convince the
jury..." you know, "They'll know
everything you've done.
They're not going to vote for
you anyways.
Everyone is mad at you at this
point."
You know, "This is one way you
can redeem yourself."
Just go off.
>> Nat, tell him if he were to
give you the necklace, that
would redeem him, and we would
vote for Amanda.
>> Who would fall for that?
Like, I feel stupid listening to
you right now.
>> Ozzy, Jason, and Erik.
He belongs in that threesome.
He belongs in that trio.
>> You're good at this, Nat.
>> Yeah, but, I mean, this is
just ridiculous.
I mean, I'll try it, but... I'll
say I talked to Cirie about it,
she's down with voting Amanda.
>> But the only way I'll go
along is if he saves you.
>> Right, right, right, right.
>> Because I don't believe him.
I have to see him save you to
believe that he'll vote Amanda,
because of all the stuff he's
been saying.
Perfect.
>> I think it could work.
>> It depends on how good you
are with this right here.
>> Honestly, I'm on my way home
packing tonight.
But I had the most harebrained
idea.
>> Okay.
>> I'll run it by you, you make
your decision.
>> Harebrained.
I can relate.
>> It's crazy.
>> Okay.
>> But it's brilliant.
Myself or Amanda are your
biggest threats, right?
That's who you want...
>> That's how I feel.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, what if me, you, and
Cirie vote Amanda tonight?
>> Okay.
>> This is where it gets funny
and tricky.
You give me your necklace.
>> I'm not even going to
consider that.
>> Just hear me out.
If you give me your necklace
tonight, Cirie said she would
hands down vote for Amanda.
That's all we need.
>> What's wrong with voting for
Amanda without me giving up the
necklace?
Everybody thinks I'm an idiot
right now.
>> I'm just thinking jury votes
for you.
Because you're riding this thing
all the way to the end.
>> When I get there, I'm not
going to have anybody.
>> Right.
We were thinking you
redeem yourself with the jury.
I just think it would be a huge,
pivotal move for you.
Because you're going to need a
pivotal move if you want a jury
vote.
>> Mm-hmm.
I have felt like I don't have a
lot of jury votes.
>> Yeah.
>> All right, let me talk to
Cirie.
>> At this point, Amanda is a
threat.
There's no question.
What is the problem with me
keeping immunity and still
voting Amanda?
>> Because I don't... I don't
know if I would believe that you
would vote Amanda.
>> Right.
>> I wish I could, like, trust
you in the fact of just you
saying it, but you kind of...
>> Blew that up.
>> ...took that all away.
>> My word isn't good anymore.
>> No.
>> And I'm all sketchy.
>> Exactly.
>> I'm like this.
>> So what do I do?
Do I... that's why it has to be
that way.
I mean, I know it's hard to ask
somebody to give up immunity,
but for me, if you were to save
Nat, then I would believe you,
and that would cue me that we're
all going to vote Amanda.
We've thrown the line out to
Erik, and I think he's nibbling
around the edges.
>> I have to think about it.
>> Yeah, of course, I'm sure.
If Erik takes that necklace off,
his torch would be snuffed so
quick, I don't even think he
could have time to blink his
eyes.
Oh, I just don't know, you know?
Erik is a pretty smart guy.
So it's like a 50-50 shot.
Him being blasted at tribal
could push him over the edge.
Even if he doesn't make up his
mind before we go, at tribal,
you and Parvati blast him, and
me and Natalie won't so he can
be thinking, like, "Maybe this
will be a good move."
>> Okay.
>> That's all I want to say.
I don't want him to see me
talking to you.
>> I'm scared about immunity,
the hidden immunity.
Because I feel like Parvati
found it, and she has it, and
she's going to give it to
Amanda.
What is the possibility that you
guys will vote Parv with me
instead of Amanda?
>> Well, if it makes more sense
and you feel more comfortable
going a different route.
>> Right.
Like, I feel like all the girls
like, "Let's get Erik."
>> I get your concern.
I get you having to angle out
every possible angle.
I get it.
>> I'm still scared... I'm just
being honest.
That's my fear.
>> No, I get it, but just go out
on a limb.
Go out on a limb.
>> I don't know.
>> He's worried about the hidden
immunity, and he would feel much
better if the three of us voted
for Parv.
He is afraid Parv's going to
pull the idol.
>> All right, I'll agree with
anything right now.
Girl, we've got him on a hook.
We've got him on the hook.
We've just got to reel him in.
It would be the ultimate Jedi
mind trick.
I just don't know-- will he buy
it?
>> JEFF: We'll now bring in the
members of our jury.
Eliza, Ozzy, Jason, James, and
Alexis, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Erik, let's talk about the
reward challenge.
You decide to bring Amanda with
you after she had completely
worked you at the last tribal
council.
>> Well, I felt like I needed to
redeem myself, and I felt like
that she could see it as some
kind of nice gesture to kind of
bury the hatchet.
>> JEFF: So, Parvati, tell me
about your time on Exile.
>> It ended up being, like, a
little nice mini-vacation for
me.
But when I got back from Exile,
I heard about Erik running
around and making alliances with
every single person, and then
breaking their alliances, and
then switching back up, and
switching back over, when he
didn't even need to do that.
He'd won immunity for the past
three times in a row.
So I was happy to be on Exile,
actually, to be away from that.
>> JEFF: Erik, what's it feel
like to hear Parvati out you,
saying you made alliances with
everybody here, you lied to
everybody here, and all the
women are nodding their head
going, "Yep, yep, yep, yep"?
>> I was nodding my head with
them, because everyone
basically turned around and went
to each other and said, "Hey,
Erik's full of crap.
Erik's telling everybody what
they want to hear."
It was stupid.
It was just a mistake.
And I feel like I need to come
to this tribal tonight and ask
for some kind of forgiveness,
some kind of "I'm sorry."
>> The thing, is Erik your word
means nothing to anybody anymore
at all.
>> Exactly.
>> You say you're sorry, and,
like, take me on a reward, and
that's great and all, but you
only took me to get my vote on
the jury.
And not only that, but
everything that you were telling
me on the reward you've told
her, you've told her, you've
told her.
>> Well, that's what I'm coming
forward about right now.
That's what I'm trying to say
right now.
>> But it's too late!
Don't you see?
>> I mean, you've just lost a
lot of respect among the women
here you're sitting with.
>> I know this.
It's not like I can't... and I'm
not going to deny it right now.
I'm not going to pretend I did
not say the things that I said.
>> Because you can't!
>> Because I can't, exactly.
I mean, game aside, I'm hoping
there's some sense of
forgiveness, some sense of,
"We'll try and trust you again."
>> You can't say, "Game aside,"
because we're playing this game.
>> That's true.
>> We're in this game right now.
You can't say, "Game aside, I
apologize."
This is the game.
>> I'm sorry.
I am sorry.
I just want to tell you that, if
it means anything at all.
>> JEFF: Erik, what's it going
to take for you to actually win
this game?
>> That's been a question that's
concerned me.
I mean, I'm looking down the
road here to the final, and I
don't see any friendly faces.
I don't see anybody on the jury
that's going to say, "Hey, you
did a pretty good job."
Or, "You didn't backstab me,"
or, "You didn't lie to my face."
And especially after what I did
to piss everybody off here.
I mean, I need some kind of
redemption before I can have a
chance of considering myself in
the finals.
>> JEFF: Cirie, is it realistic
to say, "I'm sorry?"
Does it matter if you redeem
yourself?
>> I think it does matter, Jeff,
because, ultimately, it lies in
the hands of the people who are
voted out this late and become
jury members.
So I think you are able to
redeem yourself, and I think
it's really important that you
do, especially if you've been
discredited.
If you've been discredited, the
words you say means absolutely
nothing.
It's your actions that will show
and prove what's really going
on.
>> JEFF: All right, let's get to
the vote.
Erik, you have the individual
immunity necklace.
As always, you can give it up to
somebody if you choose to.
Otherwise, it is yours, and you
are safe tonight.
>> This is a very tough decision
for me, for a lot of reasons.
As a competitor, I always say,
"You know what?
Keep your fate in our own
hands."
But there is so much weighing on
my mind.
I've made a lot of mistakes in
the past couple days.
And I know that actions do speak
louder than words.
I want to give individual
immunity to Natalie.
>> JEFF: Suddenly, Natalie, you
are safe.
Big change right before the
vote.
Natalie is now safe from the
Everybody else is fair game.
And it is time to vote.
Erik, you're up.
>> I'm voting for Parvati.
You've got to take some risks
sometime and hope people keep
their word.
Oh, god!
>> I don't even know what to
say.
But thank you.
>> You know...
>> My mother always told me,
"You may not be able to beat
them with these all time, but
you can always beat them with
this."
Sorry.
>> You're crazy!
You officially go down as the
dumbest survivor ever in the
history of Survivor, ever.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> JEFF: If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Erik.
Parvati.
One vote Erik, one vote Parvati.
Erik.
Two votes Erik.
13th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury, Erik.
That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> You guys drive me crazy.
>> I've lost my reign as dumbest
survivor ever.
>> I should have known better.
>> JEFF: Erik, the tribe has
spoken.
>> JEFF: I think that is what
you call a life lesson.
Three days left in this game.
Who knows what is going to
happen?
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
The season with the most
injuries, evacuations...
Jason.
...and blindsides...
Alexis.
...will end with the finale.
>> Damn, damn!
They got me!
I should have known better.
Those damn girls.
I mean, there's one thing to be
said about surviving the
elements and there's another
thing to be said about surviving
four crazy, sexy women.
I never thought I would be
shoulder to shoulder with all
these people that I've seen on
TV.
These are my heroes.
And they're talking to me.
They acknowledged me as a
person.
This whole experience is
undescribable.