>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> I'm not going to fight with
these kids.
They hate us.
>> PROBST: When the fans' camp
was filled with disarray...
>> Everyone is tired.
Everyone is hungry.
>> We need to fix our shelter.
>> PROBST: ...Joel was vocal
about getting the group back
together.
>> Why is everybody talking all
the time and not working?
>> PROBST: At Malakal, two
couples came together
strategically and romantically,
creating a formidable alliance.
>> I think we'll be receiving
birth announcements from Ando
and her little Ozzlets that
she's about to have.
And Parvati and James will be at
the wedding as soon as this is
over.
>> PROBST: Jonathan, Yau-Man,
Eliza, and Ami created a second
alliance...
>> Hands in.
I'll do it.
>> PROBST: And both sides needed
Cirie to gain a majority.
>> I don't care.
I'll get rid of anybody, as long
as it's not me.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, the favorites won
easily.
Favorites win immunity!
With the fans facing tribal
council, Mikey B. attempted to
control the vote.
>> Let's get the final plan
right now, and then we don't
have to talk about it again.
>> PROBST: But after watching
Mikey B. form a close bond with
Mary, Joel had other ideas.
>> Mikey thinks he's running
this whole show.
He and Mary have to be broken
up.
Mary's going home.
Mikey will be completely
confused as to what happened.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Joel's plan worked.
Second person voted out of
Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites,
Mary.
And a stunned Mikey B. watched
his closest ally go home.
18 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Be careful right here, you
guys-- right here.
>> I can only assume the big guy
Joel stuck a knife in my back
already.
Interesting.
I don't blame the move, okay,
you know, as long as the move is
not you to take that whole crew.
That would be you with four
girls and a kid, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> And Chet is included as a
girl.
Joel is playing a long game
right now when he should be
focusing on a short game.
When it gets down to the merge,
you get rid of the strong ones.
When it's team versus team, you
keep your strength and you get
rid of your weakness.
And these people-- Tracy, Kathy,
and Chet-- are weak around camp,
and they're weak in the
challenges.
They're all useless.
I know it's a million bucks, but
you're not going to win with
them.
I mean, you're not doing it.
>> Mikey thinks he's got all the
answers, and he guarantees I'll
never make it to the final four,
and he just thinks he's got this
whole tribe in his pocket.
>> I consider it that you made a
move that you didn't have to
make, okay, necessarily.
And you know, if you want to
make up for it, you can.
>> And I would really, really
like to see the look on his face
when the baseball bat comes
swinging up beside him and wakes
him up to the reality that he
doesn't have this tribe in his
pocket.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> ...needed to be under.
>> I'm glad you guys told me to
come down.
I was, like, hanging out with
the old people.
I'm only 24.
I mean, not old, not old,
just...
>> They go to bed early.
>> Just tired of that damn cave.
>> Amanda, Ozzy, James, and
Parvati said they were going to
go down to the beach, and they
said, "Come with us.
It will be fun."
So I went down there with them,
and they were working me.
>> Right.
>> You dislike Jonathan that
much, huh?
>> They were like, "You know, I
think we need to keep this team
strong, and I think the two
weakest people are Yau-Man and
Cirie.
I think we need to get them out
of here."
And I kind of was like, "Oh,
yeah, sure, okay."
I listened to them, but I don't
trust them.
They'd be stupid to stick with
us knowing that the five of us
are so tight.
>> So what's the proposal?
>> They've been working.
They've been trying.
>> Unless they think that they
have a chance with Cirie.
>> Well, there's definitely a
little bit of juggling the two
foursomes, because they need my
vote, either side.
And I'm still trying to figure
out which side is better for me.
>> If we get another vote, then
Parvati's going to go, right?
>> For sure.
>> She's weak enough and... and
threatening enough because of
her relationships with Ozzy and
with James.
>> And with Amanda.
I mean, the two of them have
been bonding.
>> As long as the five of us
stay strong, and we are, then
we're cool.
>> In this game, for me, it's
all about who I think I can
trust.
And if I feel that I can trust
you, then I'm willing to go all
the way with you.
But if I don't trust you, then
you can't believe a word I tell
you.
>> Tree mail!
>> Uh-oh!
>> This is a big tree mail, you
guys.
>> Big tree mail.
>> Okay, it says, "Preparing to
go into battle, use war paint
and a battle cry.
Are you ready to tackle your
enemy?"
Oh!
"You better be ready to try.
So pick three choices for your
reward.
Today will be an aggressive
meeting.
If you win, you take them home.
Lose, and you just take a
beating."
>> Okay.
>> It's our wrestling one that
we've wanted for so long.
>> This is our comfort
catalogue.
>> Ah!
Wow.
>> How many do we get to pick?
>> Three.
>> We get to pick three?
>> Oh, God!
>> We get three things, guys.
>> Right.
>> That's awesome.
>> All right!
>> Ready?
Shelter-- tarp and rope.
>> Tarp and rope would be good.
>> Sleeping items-- blankets,
pillows, mattress.
We've got to use our war paint,
and we've got to come up with a
battle cry.
>> Yes!
>> We're going to war.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, it's war.
>> Y'all better get serious
about this.
>> It should be like... just
like a little, bitty heart.
>> Are you ready to bring it?
>> Let's do it!
>> We are going to kick some ass
today.
>> I know.
>> There's no way we're going to
lose today.
We're going to decimate them.
We have the will.
We've been dry.
We've been eating.
>> Ah!
>> There's no way we're losing
this challenge.
>> We lost our last challenge.
Morale is a little bit down.
But you can't fight emotionally.
You have to fight logically.
And logically, if somebody comes
and invades my home, I'm going
to kill them.
>> Malakal!
Malakal!
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Favorites getting your first
look at the new tribe of fans.
Mary voted out at the last
tribal council.
>> Mary?
>> PROBST: This morning in tree
mail, you were both given war
paint.
Glad to see you put it to good
use, because today is going to
be a battle.
For today's challenge, both
tribes will start at opposite
ends of a lagoon in their
opponent's end zone.
On my go, you will charge across
the lagoon toward the other
tribe carrying three canvas
bags.
Your goal is to get your three
bags, plus two bags from the
other tribe, into your end zone.
You are allowed to steal bags
from your opponent's end zone
even after they've scored.
First tribe to get five bags in
their end zone at the same time
wins reward.
This morning, in tree mail, you
were also given a catalog, told
to choose three items.
Here's what the favorites are
playing for: shelter, lighting
kit, survival kit.
Here's what the fans are playing
for.
They chose differently: fishing
kit, shelter, and a kitchen set.
Winning tribe gets their three
items.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Let's get it on.
All right!
Got a little bit of rain to make
it more fun.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Who's going to square off
against who?
Joel knocks Yau-Man and takes
Amanda down hard.
This is getting physical quick.
James pulls Kathy off Cirie.
Favorites have two bags in their
end zone, fans have one.
Got to get five bags in at once.
Yau-Man on a breakaway.
Yau-Man in to the end zone.
Favorites have three bags, fans
have one.
Joel and James going at it.
James trying to take Joel down.
Joel tosses the bag.
Big collision!
Joel steals one from the
favorites.
We're now back to favorites two,
fans have one.
Joel pulls Amanda down hard.
Been some hard hits already.
Fans with two bags.
Favorites with two bags.
We're tied up, two bags each.
Jason has it.
Hands it off to Alexis.
Oh!
A huge collision with Penner.
Heads knocked on that one.
Penner pulling Alexis back.
That was the biggest collision
so far.
James just comes in and busts up
the whole pile.
Erik steals a bag from the
favorites.
Erik is literally pulling Eliza
into the end zone.
Fans have three bags, favorites
with two.
You need five to win.
>> Get him!
>> PROBST: Amanda going after
Erik, who tosses Amanda over his
head.
That irritates James.
James now in on it.
James grabbing Erik.
Mikey B. in on it.
Alexis steals one from the
favorites.
>> Come on!
Run, run, run!
>> PROBST: Alexis knocks Eliza
down.
We are 4-2.
Fans need one more bag.
James trying to steal that bag.
He's pulling three people in the
water.
James has the bag for the
favorites!
We're tied 3-3.
Amanda trying to steal the bag
from Mikey B.
Amanda steals the bag for the
favorites.
Kathy tries to tackle Amanda.
Amanda tosses the bag to James.
It is now 4-2.
Favorites now have four bags.
They need just one more.
Favorites have their hands on
that fifth and final bag.
Penner fighting for it!
Penner's got it!
This will do it!
Favorites win reward!
A huge battle comes to an end.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Nice work.
Now you must choose one member
from the fans tribe to go to
Exile Island.
Who are you going to send to
Exile?
>> We're going to send KB.
>> PROBST: Kathy, you don't look
pleased at all with that news.
>> No.
>> PROBST: Now who are you going
to send from your own tribe?
Ami, you're excited to go to
Exile?
>> I am-- second clue.
>> PROBST: All right, Kathy and
Ami head out.
Boat's waiting for you.
You will rejoin your tribe at
the next immunity challenge.
All right, fans, got nothing for
you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Good job, guys.
Hell of a battle.
>> PROBST: Favorites,
congratulations.
You have shelter, a lighting
kit, and a survival kit.
Come get your stuff, head back
to camp.
>> The nice girl, we got tangled
up, and she's like, "So do you
have a girlfriend?"
>> Well, Mike had both me and
Amanda.
He had two of us, like, wrapped
up, and we were both struggling
to get free, and he's like, "I'd
like to stay like this all day."
>> Holy crap.
That was like the hardest thing
I've ever done.
>> I don't know if the other
people feel relaxed because they
feel secure in their alliances,
but I don't feel relaxed at all.
I feel like I have to
continuously scramble to make
sure everything works in my
favor.
>> You were just terminating,
like, throwing people left and
right.
I was very impressed.
>> Because I am in the middle
right now, I have to look at
every option or every scenario
that could possibly happen and
try to have a plan B.
If I was in their position, I
think they could do a little
more for me, actually.
No one's washing my clothes.
I haven't gotten any special
meals.
I think if they really wanted my
vote, they should probably do a
little more.
I should probably be carried,
like, on a chariot-type thing.
All right, ladies, I'm just
feeling a little bit nervous,
and it's only because of the
relationships that you already
have with James and you, Amanda,
have with Ozzy.
But, Parvati, this James thing
just kind of developed.
>> Right.
>> That's the thing...
>> I know.
>> I'm just going to put it out
there.
I like flirting with Ozzy.
So if that makes you
uncomfortable, then I'll, like,
stop, but...
>> No, no, no, no, don't change.
>> No, because that's the way
you keep him close, you know?
And he doesn't asks questions.
James asks me no questions.
>> Are you nervous about her?
>> No, I'm not.
>> She's like me a little.
She gets paranoid.
She needs to be reassured a lot.
>> Let's reassure her.
>> Okay.
But they're out there filling
her head with lies.
>> I want to vote Yau.
>> You want to vote Yau?
>> Because if Yau goes to Exile
Island one time...
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Going up against Yau...
>> You'll never win.
>> Yeah.
>> So I have both of you guys'
word that it's us three to the
end.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't care if James
proposes to you or you and Ozzy
have little Ozzlets.
>> Oh, you know how I am.
>> All right.
>> So we'll talk to her.
They're filling her head with
stuff.
She's the swing vote, I guess.
And why would she swing over to
them unless she thinks that she
should be the queen bee over
there?
>> Yeah, but she's not.
She won't be.
>> Well, exactly.
>> I hope she doesn't fall for
their garbage.
>> What's it say?
>> It says-- okay, listen good--
"Continue your quest by crossing
the ocean."
>> I'm here on Exile Island
again.
Right away, Ami wanted to go to
the other island.
After having been to that island
many times with Cirie, I'm
like... because Cirie and I
found all four clues.
>> It says, "Cross the ocean."
So that's what we've done
before.
>> Yeah.
Ami saw the clue up in the tree,
and she could not figure it out,
but I had to play dumb, you
know, like, "I don't know."
I was just exhausted, and I
wasn't about to go island
hopping again.
>> I think we should, because
the tide's coming in, not out.
>> The waves started getting
choppy.
I said to Ami, "Uh-oh."
I'm no weatherman, but the
clouds, everything, it looked
like a big storm was coming in.
So pretty much clue searching
had to come to an end.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, mother of God.
>> This is insane.
>> It's pouring down rain.
Our shelter sucks.
Everyone's freezing.
Everyone's cold.
Everyone's sopping wet.
Not much you can do.
>> Oh, wow, it sucks in here.
>> It sprinkled last night.
Tonight it's a monsoon.
Oh, right on my face!
>> Yay, victory!
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Came up to the cave and
settled down for a nice sleep.
The rain is falling really,
really, really, really hard, the
hardest since we've been here.
>> We're totally covered.
Oh, my God, this is so great.
>> This is amazing.
>> Oh!
>> And I kind of feel bad for
the whole Airai tribe.
I know that they are probably
not doing well right now.
>> I'm sure the other tribe is
doing really well, staying dry
and probably laughing about us
right now having to endure this
wicked storm.
I just hope no spiders get me--
or scorpions or rats.
>> Last night was probably the
worst night that we've had since
we've been here.
It rained all night, and the
shelter didn't do one single bit
of good.
>> Oh, God!
>> This morning, we feel like we
got beat up twice yesterday--
once by the other tribe and once
by nature.
>> Glorious evening, huh?
>> I didn't sleep at all.
Did y'all?
>> No.
>> My fingers are prune-y from
it being so wet.
>> Oh, I know.
>> I bet the water is warmer.
How did you sleep on the boat?
>> Huh?
>> How did you sleep on the
boat?
>> Oh, fine.
>> Not the sort of night you
want to have before a challenge,
and this one's for immunity.
I think that people are pretty
demoralized right now.
We cannot lose today.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Ami and
Kathy, returning from Exile
Island.
( applause )
>> We had to just sleep in the
rain.
>> Love you guys.
>> PROBST: Ready to get to it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
I know you're hiding that idol
back there, Amanda.
>> I know.
I'm trying to keep it from you.
We'll get it back.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, each
tribe will choose two men and
two women.
Their job will be to hold to a
very heavy rope net while
members of the other tribe
attempt to shoot coconuts into
the net.
The more coconuts you get into
the other tribe's net, the
heavier that net will become.
The tribe that holds on the
longest wins immunity,
guaranteed at least one more
night in this game.
Losers go to tribal council.
Somebody will be voted out.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
Holding the net for the fans:
Erik, Natalie, Tracy, and Joel.
For the favorites: Parvati,
James, Jonathan Penner, and
Cirie.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Come on, Ozzy.
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Mikey B. up
first.
Learning curve.
You want to get as many coconuts
in the other tribe's net as you
can.
Jason connects for the fans.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: The more coconuts,
the heavier that net will
become.
>> God, that's heavy.
>> PROBST: A little harder to
throw a coconut than you'd
think.
Alexis connects for the fans.
Eliza just misses.
>> Come on, Amanda!
>> You almost got it!
>> That wasn't correct, Amanda.
>> PROBST: Jason showing them
how it's done.
Yau-Man finally breaks the
spell.
Favorites are on the board.
Kathy just misses for the fans.
Ami gets one in.
Now the favorites are on a roll.
Alexis drills another one.
>> Yeah, you're good, little
one.
>> PROBST: Eliza goes underhand.
>> Yeah, Eliza!
>> PROBST: Chet!
Nobody missing.
>> Sweet lord, Chet!
Yes, Ozzy!
Yes!
Come on, Kathy, show us how it's
done in Wisconsin.
Chet, we're at a pageant
and... Chet!
>> PROBST: Penner talking a lot
of trash-- just what we expect.
>> Nice shot there, squirrely
boy.
>> PROBST: Reminds me of the
Cook Islands.
Nets starting to get heavier
now.
How's it going, James?
>> I'm chillin'.
>> PROBST: Yeah.
>> Always.
>> PROBST: Fans having to
readjust a little bit.
>> Come on, guys.
Let's speed it up.
>> Come on, Oz.
Nice.
>> PROBST: Ozzy puts another one
in.
Jason banks another one for the
fans.
Amanda connects.
Kathy connects.
>> Nice shot, Kathy.
>> PROBST: Everybody putting
coconuts in the net.
Weight starting to get heavy
now.
Starting to show.
Starting to take its toll now.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Parvati, James,
Penner, and Cirie now starting
to struggle a bit.
>> Sink it, Mike!
>> PROBST: Fans starting to put
some weight in that favorites
net.
Erik, Natalie, Tracy, Joel
struggle a bit.
>> Come on, guys.
You got to sink those.
>> PROBST: Parvati, James,
Penner, Cirie struggling.
Mikey B. adds more weight.
>> Just a couple more, guys--
couple more!
>> PROBST: James trying to hold
on.
Parvati trying to hold on.
Chet puts another one in for the
fans.
>> Hold it!
>> PROBST: That's it!
Fans win immunity!
( fans cheering )
>> That's what I'm talking
about.
>> We won!
>> Oh, my god!
>> PROBST: Fans,
congratulations.
( cheering and applause )
>> All right!
>> PROBST: Immunity, nobody
going home, nobody going to
tribal council.
Favorites, you know the drill.
Tribal council, one of you will
be voted out.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Today we lost the immunity
challenge, which sucks.
It was hard enough just coming
back from Exile Island after the
night that I had, but then
coming back, losing a challenge,
and having to go to tribal
council tonight-- I mean, does
it get worse on Survivor?
>> She's sleeping with James,
and we can't have it.
You know, we just can't have
that.
I'm sorry.
It's a dumb play on her part.
Do you agree?
>> All right.
>> And we're cool, right, you
and me?
>> We're cool.
>> I think we should just stick
with the plan.
>> Okay, stick with the plan,
stick with the plan.
>> Cirie wants Yau-Man gone,
so... we need her.
>> Yeah, but that's her play.
>> And he's going to go to Exile
before the next immunity
challenge.
There's just a strong
possibility it's going to
happen.
>> Yeah, but still...
>> And I know they want to vote
me out.
>> Yeah, they're after your ass,
baby.
>> Better not!
>> I just... I feel like Eliza
would be a better choice.
Yau-Man's stronger.
>> Eliza, we can get rid of
Eliza any day.
>> I know, but if we keep Yau-
Man, the chances of having a
good run at an immunity
challenge are better.
Eliza is not good at challenges.
>> He's out for himself.
>> I swear, we can vote Eliza
next.
>> And he'll sneak by.
>> We can, anybody you want, but
I cannot stay here and see him
find another idol and not be
able to go, and I thought we
were all cool on that.
>> What do you think?
>> Yeah, I mean, if you guys
really feel that way.
>> I feel.
>> Which one?
>> Yau.
>> Or Jonathan, either one.
>> What's going on, dudes?
>> What's up, man?
>> I didn't mean to break up the
party.
>> Oh, you didn't.
>> You all right?
>> Okay, we're going to do some
girl stuff.
>> Me or Yau?
So who's she voting for, me or
Yau?
>> I don't know.
>> Just tell me, is it me or is
it Yau?
>> I don't know.
They're trying to decide.
That's what they were talking
about when you walked up.
>> I'm starting to feel a little
antsy about the vote, only
because I'd like to believe that
Cirie is tight with us, but
obviously Amanda and Parvati
have been pouring a lot of BS
into her ear, and you know, you
have to hope that Cirie is, I
don't know, smart enough, loyal
enough, happy enough to stick
with our group.
It's going to be the five of us
to vote off Parvati because
she's got these two guys wrapped
around her finger.
It's that simple.
Now, I don't know what they've
said to you about our
trustworthiness or our desire to
vote you out.
I don't know what they've said,
okay?
>> Uh-huh.
>> It's not true.
Please, because we've been a
solid five.
The plan is a good one.
It's simply not true.
>> Those two pairs together--
right?-- forms a core four.
>> You know, I hear that.
>> There's no way you could work
yourself into it.
I mean, as soon as they've got
the vote, they're going to take
you out.
>> But you know what, Yau?
The same argument that you're
using, they use the same
argument.
So why should I believe this one
over that one?
>> I'm not going to use an
argument.
I'm going to use common sense.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Honestly, the five of us
should march forward together.
There's no reason not to.
We have... I have no hidden
agenda.
I have no interest in voting any
of the four of you out.
That's the god's honest truth.
>> I know that you and Yau have
y'all little thing, and if you
want to stand here and say that
y'all don't...
>> But there's only the two of
us.
>> Cirie, Cirie...
>> Okay.
>> Hold on, hold on, hold on.
>> That's my thing.
That's my thing.
>> I appreciate that.
I appreciate that.
>> Keep it real.
>> Let's keep it real.
>> Yeah.
>> I think that you and I have a
little thing, okay?
I think that Ami and I have a
little thing.
It's ridiculous!
>> Call it what you want.
>> I'm going to.
I'm going to.
>> And being like that is not
really going to get my vote,
seriously.
>> Listen, wait a second.
We have a long way to go.
It's day...
>> I know.
I played.
Just like you played, I played
too.
How far did you go?
>> I don't know, maybe not as
far as you.
>> I've seen everybody.
I may look like I'm laughing and
joking and playing, but I'm
watching everybody, and I know
that what you have... I know
there's no way you would vote
him out before me.
I know it ain't.
>> I don't... you know what?
I thought we were solid.
And they've come up, and they've
said stuff to you that has put
doubt into your mind.
But I have not done anything to
you to put that doubt into your
mind.
>> I just...
>> I'm trying... you know, you
want to keep it real.
I'm trying to keep it real.
>> I have, I have.
This is why we're having this
conversation.
>> Well, I am keeping it real.
We're having a conversation.
>> I'm going to change, and I'm
going to think, and I just need,
like, five minutes without all
the stuff.
( Cirie sighing )
>> I mean, let's take Yau-Man
out tonight if that's the way
it's got to be, but Parvati...
>> I don't think that's a good
idea.
>> I don't think so either.
So who's it going to be?
>> I think Eliza is the obvious
choice.
>> All right.
>> If you guys were to vote for
Parvati, it's going to be
throwing votes away, and it will
be Yau-Man who goes home,
because they will have numbers.
>> You know, I hear what you're
saying about your relationship
with her, you know, but I'm
talking about the fact that
she's got you in her corner, and
she's got James, and it's
dangerous.
You know, Eliza's not a threat.
I mean, you're right, she's the
weakest link, but she's also the
least threatening link.
You know what I mean?
I mean, that's just the way I've
been think about it, but I can
rethink it, I guess.
>> Cirie is not going to change
her vote.
She's voting for Yau.
>> That's fine.
>> We have to vote with her.
>> I'm not... I'm voting for
Eliza.
I have to.
I think that's the right thing
to do.
I think that to keep us strong
is to vote out Eliza.
>> But Cirie's not budging on
Yau.
She's voting Yau-Man.
If we don't...
>> We don't need Cirie.
>> If we don't vote with her...
>> Then what?
>> ...she's not going to...
she'll never trust us.
>> Who's she going to trust,
someone other than the five of
us?
>> I just don't think it's a
good thing if we vote different
people.
I just think we all need to vote
the same person.
>> I don't think it's good, too,
that she's, like, setting this
decision.
Like, what's up with that?
>> I don't think that's right.
>> Next time it's going to be
all her decision, too?
>> No.
>> You see what I'm saying,
though?
Like, I didn't like that.
>> I agree.
Let's talk to her right now.
>> Who?
>> Cirie.
>> What?
>> All five of us need to talk.
>> The more that I think about
it, the more it seems like it
makes more sense to vote Eliza.
>> Eliza, please?
Please, please.
>> Come on, Cirie.
>> Why is it so...
>> Because we need the strength
right now.
>> For challenges.
>> We're going to be on man
short.
>> It doesn't matter, but we all
need to be on the same page as
far as the five of us.
>> I really... honestly, I don't
want to change my vote.
I don't feel threatened by Eliza
at all.
>> That's not sticking together,
though.
>> My vote has never changed.
Your votes changed.
>> Cirie is killing me.
You can't be the boss of
everything, and everybody just
let her go, let her go, and let
her go.
She went from the swing vote to
the one who's deciding what's
going on for the whole group.
That can't happen.
This feels like I'm in China
again, messing with a bunch of
dumbasses.
>> I'm not sure we can't still
get Parvati out with four.
I'm not sure.
Because they're split between...
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Some folks want to vote for
Yau, and some folks want to vote
for you.
Four votes for her may be
enough.
>> They're not going to go into
tribal split.
That's the dumbest thing ever.
They're not that stupid.
>> They were kind of talking
like they might.
>> Craziness, craziness before
the vote.
Well, the four of us, the
remaining four of the five, not
including Cirie, are going to
stay tight and vote for Parvati.
>> What's going on?
>> Because right now, the other
group, including Cirie, are
split.
Some of them want to vote Eliza
out as the weakest link.
Some of them want to vote Yau-
Man out as either the weakest
link or the biggest threat.
I'm not sure why they would vote
Yau-Man out.
Come on, go be productive.
You're being paranoid.
If we can keep them split, if we
can keep them from coming to a
consensus, our four votes would
actually be enough to get
Parvati out.
Our four votes may actually win
the day.
That's what I'm hoping for,
fingers crossed.
>> PROBST: Penner, got to ask,
how disappointing is it to be
back here?
>> It's terrible.
After that big victory yesterday
that felt so great and so
earned, today was a tough day
after that loss.
>> PROBST: James, do the fans
earn a bit of respect from you
guys that they are here to play
as well?
>> Yeah, they have definitely
earned some respect.
They got a little more hunger in
them.
We're dry, and we have food, and
I guess it's made us kind of
soft.
We do need to win and make sure
that the favorites are on the
top at the end, and they're
winning right now, and I don't
like it.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, have you
isolated a problem why you're
losing?
>> We need to really, really be
hungry for the win.
Whenever we won anything, we
were all very happy for, you
know, a day, and then once we
lost, happened to be the more
critical ones, and I feel very
vulnerable every time we lose.
>> PROBST: Penner, there's two
ideas going on early in the
game.
Is this more about "Let's all
try to stay together," or is it
"I'm going to win this game, one
way or another"?
>> I think some of us would like
to stay together and make this
tribe as strong as possible.
And I think that some of us are
making moves already to
eliminate people that they
consider threats to them and
take control of the game.
>> PROBST: Cirie, where are you
sitting on this?
>> For me, Jeff, I'm looking at
it as far as the tribe and as
far as myself in this game.
And if I'm not playing the game
that's going to benefit you the
most, it doesn't mean that I'm
not doing what's best for the
tribe.
>> PROBST: Penner, you had a lot
of reactions during that
comment.
>> I mean, she's made a move
today that will advance her in
the game and put her in a power
position, and I don't think
anybody believes that voting out
the person that she wants to
vote out is going to make the
tribe stronger.
>> For me, Jeff, had I made the
move that he wanted me to make,
we wouldn't even be having this
conversation.
>> I thought you were in an
alliance, and you flopped, and
then you brought everybody over.
You did.
>> Is this not the pot calling
the kettle black?
Whatever.
>> I don't know.
I thought I was in an alliance
with you.
Until today, I was.
>> Jonathan, I came into your
alliance as the fifth person,
and I'm supposed to trust you.
>> Were you in the alliance?
Were you in the alliance?
Did you say you were in the
alliance and working with us and
that we were solid and all that?
You did.
>> I did, I did.
>> Okay, that's all I want to
say.
>> I did, but I don't trust you,
point blank, period.
>> And now you've asked everyone
else to help you vote off the
person that is a threat...
>> I didn't ask anybody
anything.
>> Please.
>> We all came to a decision to
vote who we vote... who we're
voting.
>> Because you said you weren't
going to vote for anybody else.
That's the only person you were
going to vote for.
>> You told me the best thing
for this tribe was to get rid of
Parvati.
>> I still believe that.
>> And because I didn't do that,
this is why we're having that
conversation.
>> I'm only trying to make moves
to make this tribe stronger.
>> I'm not doing what you want
me to do.
I don't trust you as far as I
can pick you up and throw you.
Sorry.
And if you're upset that they
trust me, too bad.
>> I'm not upset.
I'm upset that you are going to
now be in the driver's seat.
>> Because I'm not voting the
way you want me to vote.
>> Anybody can vote any way they
want.
>> They should.
I don't have mind control over
anybody here.
So y'all all vote however you
want to vote.
>> Right, I would urge everyone
to vote their conscience.
Then we have some common ground
that we can work from.
Otherwise, it's going to be, I
think, a much bigger split and
kind of disastrous.
So I'm hoping that people do
vote the way they honestly
believe this tribe is going to
be the strongest.
>> Everybody here knows it was
split.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: Parvati, during this
whole thing, you had a look on
your face like "I just wish this
would go away."
>> Yeah.
I mean, people are concerned
that maybe I'm just flirting and
manipulating other people to,
you know, make alliances and get
people on my side.
So yeah, I know that my name has
been brought up.
And that scares me, but that
doesn't surprise me at all.
>> PROBST: Well, it sounds like
however it goes down, it's going
to be a very big vote for this
tribe.
Let's get to it.
It is time to vote.
Amanda, you're up.
>> I have nothing against you,
Parvati, but I think that by
following Cirie, you have signed
your own death warrant.
She's led you like a sheep to
the slaughter and played you
like a fiddle.
I'm sorry for you.
>> You aligning with the biggest
liar in the game made me feel
like strategically this was the
best move for me.
Sorry.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol, now is the time
to play it.
Once votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the tribal council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Parvati.
Yau-Man.
That's two votes Yau-Man.
Parvati.
Two votes Parvati.
Two votes Yau-Man.
Cirie.
Two votes Parvati, two votes
Yau-Man, one vote Cirie.
Yau-Man.
That's three votes Yau-Man, two
votes Parvati, one vote Cirie.
Yau-Man.
That's four votes Yau-Man, two
votes Parvati, one vote Cirie.
Third person voted out of Fans
vs. Favorites, Yau-Man.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Great playing with you.
Don't worry.
Don't cry.
>> PROBST: Yau-Man, the tribe
has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good luck, you guys.
Have fun.
>> PROBST: Well, the problem
with this tribe is no secret.
You guys are divided.
Big question is what are you
going to do about it?
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> I don't have to hear what you
have to say.
>> What did I ever do to you
except ask you to be in an
alliance with me?
>> PROBST: ...it's Cirie versus
Jonathan....
>> You know that I broke your
alliance, done.
>> You said you were going to
get Mike off a long time okay.
>> PROBST: ...and Joel versus
Mikey B...
>> My goal is to cut his damn
head off.
>> PROBST: ...and an Exile
Island that can't be missed.
>> No hard feelings.
I had a great time.
I was a very big target coming
into this.
You know, by virtue of me doing
so well in Fiji, I consider
myself lucky.
Many people want to get on
Survivor once.
Well, I've been on twice.
But I wish I would have been in
there longer.
That's the way how this game is.
It's a very cruel game, but
that's the way it goes.