>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
( thunder )
...by day ten, the situation was
grim for the fans.
>> Everyone is freezing.
Everyone is cold.
>> PROBST: Having won no reward
challenges, they were hungry and
weak, and their inability to
build a shelter made a bad
situation worse.
>> I am sure the other tribe is
probably laughing about us right
now.
>> PROBST: A bitter power
struggle emerged between Joel
and Mikey B.
>> Mikey seems to think that
he's running the show over here,
and I have to put a stop to it.
>> PROBST: So Joel turned on
Mikey B. by arranging to have
his closest ally voted out.
>> I'll get Joel.
You mark my words about that
one.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Fans win immunity!
...the fans pulled off a
stunning upset, and the
favorites were thrown into the
hot seat.
At Malakal...
>> So should we think about
working a little bit together?
>> Oh, I definitely want to
think about that.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: ...Cirie convinced
Jonathan and his alliance that
she was with them.
>> As long as we stay strong,
then we're cool.
>> PROBST: But later she joined
the alliance of James and
Parvati and Amanda and Ozzy.
>> I want to vote Yau, because
if Yau gets to Exile Island one
time...
>> Oh, yeah.
>> ...forget about it.
>> Going up against Yau...
>> You'll never win.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: James and Ozzy wanted
to vote out Eliza, believing she
was the weakest member of the
tribe.
>> It makes more sense to vote
Eliza.
>> Eliza, please?
Please, please.
>> Come on, Cirie.
>> Why is it...
>> Because we need his strength
right now.
>> Honestly, I don't want to
change my vote.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Jonathan was angered by Cirie's
betrayal.
>> I thought I was in alliance
with you.
Until today, I was.
>> Jonathan, I came into your
alliance as the fifth person.
>> Were you in the alliance?
>> Am I supposed to trust you?
Did you say you were in the
alliance?
>> PROBST: In the end, Cirie got
one vote.
Cirie.
But she also got her way.
Third person voted out of Fans
vs. Favorites, Yau-Man.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I was, I was.
>> It was just an hour before
tribal...
>> And I was.
>> Then you changed your mind.
>> You know why?
>> But you didn't communicate
that with me.
>> Whatever.
I wasn't even talking to you.
>> What?
>> I wasn't even talking to you.
>> I'm sorry.
I'm here.
Cirie flipped.
She gave us her word that she
was tight with us.
She saw a better chance, and she
took it, at my expense.
And the truth is that she's much
more manipulative and devious
than I am.
>> And I'm trying...
>> That's kind of disgusting.
>> I don't.
I'm grown.
I don't have to hear what you
have to say.
Why do I...
>> Yes, you do.
>> No, I don't.
Jonathan is pissed off to the
hilt.
He's just mad that he couldn't
make me vote the way he wanted
me to.
>> You didn't trust me anyway.
You used me as an excuse to
flop.
>> I didn't trust you.
I'm just done.
You know that I broke your
alliance.
I don't trust you.
You don't trust me.
Everybody knows it.
Done.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> I have no idea.
>> I think Eliza, Yau-Man.
>> Eliza or Yau-Man, yeah.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's who I think too.
>> We won our immunity challenge
yesterday.
We're very, very pleased.
You know, there's been some
dissension amongst people within
the tribe, and I think this was
good for us.
>> Check it out!
>> Oh, what was that?
>> No!
Yeah!
>> Nice!
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Nice.
>> Whew!
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, you did.
Chop his head off.
>> Come and get it.
>> Yeah.
>> It's going to be like a hot
dog.
>> It better be like a hot dog.
>> Whew!
>> You always need to be pulling
your weight.
You always need to be doing what
you need to do to maintain a
position.
All I've done since I have been
here is keep my head down and
work.
This is where the rub is for me.
I don't feel like Chet really
wants to help out and carry his
weight.
How do you not say, "Dude, like,
either pick it up or go home"?
>> What?
>> That.
>> Yeah, it's about 2:00.
Time for Chet's bedtime.
Wouldn't you say?
>> I don't even know how.
If I did that and I got back, my
mom would spank me.
>> Chet is distraught and weak
and just decimated.
He is not in this game right
now.
He's a physical and mental
liability, and he's horrible for
morale around camp.
He's gone.
Chet is gone.
>> I feel really sick.
My ears are hurting.
My sinuses are hurting.
My glands are swollen.
I feel like I'm probably the
next to go if we lose another
immunity challenge because my
tribe thinks I am weak, and
being sick doesn't help that.
>> Last night at tribal council
was kind of rough, because I'm
all about keeping the strongest
people.
We kept one of the weakest
girls, Eliza, and she's sick
right now.
She's on the beach, shivering,
about to pass out.
But being that Cirie was so hell
bent on getting Yau-Man out,
kind of folded to her will,
which was a big mistake.
>> I'm just taking it easy so I
can perform really well in the
challenge.
>> But I didn't know you were so
sick.
>> It's not contagious.
>> It's not about being
contagious.
It's about being in a weaker
state.
>> But I'm going to be fine.
Even being slightly sick, I'm
still going to better at
whatever challenge we have today
than Yau-Man would have.
After they found out that I was
sick, right to my face Ozzy and
James said, "Oh, we should have
voted you out last night; we
wish we'd voted you out last
night."
So that made me feel like crap.
You know, acting like that
towards me doesn't make me want
to perform well in the
challenge.
I mean, if you were a little bit
supportive, I think that'd help.
( laughter )
>> I hate these people.
I do.
I mean, I almost hope that they
get sicker than I am and have to
be removed from the game.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Fans getting your first look at
the new tribe of favorites.
Yau-Man voted out at the last
tribal council.
>> No way.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: Here is how it works.
On my go, four members from each
tribe will swim out to a
floating platform.
One at a time, you'll dive down
to a 30-foot-long steel cage
containing tribe-colored
coconuts, ten of which have
letters painted on them.
You'll remove your tribe's
lettered coconuts from the cage
one at a time and place them in
a floating bin.
You'll then swim the bin back to
shore, where the four remaining
tribe members will use those
letters to unscramble a one-word
answer.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: I think you're going
to like it.
>> Oh, that's nice.
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: Three egg-laying
hens, one rooster.
Got some chicken feed as well.
They've already laid three eggs
since they've been here.
In addition, the winning tribe
will choose one member from the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island.
You will also select somebody
from your own tribe to join
them.
Fans, you have one extra person,
sitting somebody out.
You cannot sit out the same
person in back-to-back
challenges.
Who's it going to be?
>> I am.
>> Chet.
>> PROBST: Chet going to sit
this one out.
Give you a minute to strategize,
and we'll get started.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready.
Go!
All four tribe members have to
be on the platform before the
first person can go down.
Go.
It's Ozzy and Jason swimming out
first.
Jason making his way along the
cage.
Ozzy spending a lot of time
under water.
He's still working at the end of
the cage.
Jason up with the first coconut
for the fans.
>> Come on, Jay!
>> PROBST: Mikey B. in the water
for the fans.
Ozzy starting to make his way
forward now.
Looks like he is moving several
coconuts at once.
>> Jason!
>> Yep.
>> You know what Ozzy is doing,
right?
>> Yep.
>> Pushing all their letters
forward.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Mikey B. up with the
second coconut for the fans.
Ozzy with the first coconut for
the favorites.
Go!
Penner in the water for the
favorites.
Penner swims out to the front of
the cage, where Ozzy has pushed
a coconut forward.
Penner up with the second
coconut for the favorites.
We're tied two coconuts each.
Favorites now with three
coconuts.
And Parvati up with the fourth
coconut for the favorites.
Ozzy's strategy starting to pay
off.
Favorites lead 4-2.
Alexis has the third coconut for
the fans-- 4-3.
Jason back in the water.
Favorites now have five
coconuts.
There are ten coconuts total.
Favorites now with six coconuts.
Fans have four.
Ami in the water now.
Mikey B. in the water for the
fans.
Ami up with the seventh coconut
for the favorites.
Mikey B. up with the fifth
coconut for the fans.
It is 7-5.
Natalie up with the sixth
coconut for the fans.
It is 7-6.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Fans have worked
their way back into it.
We are tied 7-7.
Ozzy up with the eighth coconut
for the favorites.
Penner up with the ninth
coconut.
One coconut left for the
favorites.
Ozzy up with the tenth coconut
for the favorites.
Everybody out to the bin now.
Unclip and swim it back to
shore.
The favorites are on the move.
Jason up with the eighth coconut
for the fans.
Fans still have two coconuts in
the water.
Mikey B. heading out as the
favorites are already swimming
in to shore.
Start working on that puzzle.
Favorites with a big lead thanks
to Ozzy's strategy.
It is a one-word answer.
You've got to unscramble.
>> Oh, yeah, that might be it.
T-r...
>> Oh, my God.
>> All right, if I come up with
the damn puzzle, come on.
>> PROBST: Mikey B. up with the
ninth coconut for the fans.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah!
We got it!
>> We got it!
>> PROBST: James thought he knew
what it was, and he was right:
"triumphant."
Favorites win reward!
( cheers and applause )
>> Hey, how about that?
>> Oh, smarty pants.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Favorites,
congratulations.
Three hens, one rooster, chicken
feed-- up to you what you do
with them.
Big decision now.
You're going to choose one
person from the tribe of fans to
go to Exile Island.
Who's going?
>> Jeff, unfortunately, we're
sending Kathy again.
>> PROBST: Kathy's going to
Exile Island.
Favorites, who is going to join
her?
>> Ozzy.
>> PROBST: All right, Ozzy and
Kathy, get your stuff.
The boat's waiting for you.
You will rejoin your tribe at
the next immunity challenge.
Fans, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Favorites, come get your reward.
Congratulations.
>> Chicken.
>> We lost our challenge today.
It's always a bummer to lose a
challenge.
Malakal has won every reward
They've got four freaking
chickens now and eggs and
everything else.
They're living a life of luxury
out here compared to what we've
got, which is, you know, jack
squat.
>> Ozzy is insane!
He is, hands down, the best
physical competitor in survival
history.
Man.
I was, like, jealous of Kathy.
When they were like, "Yeah,
she's going to Exile," I was,
like, "She's going to eat better
than we've eaten in nine days."
>> Kathy is a weak person.
The other team definitely sees
this just by the way Kathy is.
I mean, I'm pretty confident
she's not looking for that idol
right now.
I'm pretty confident she's
curled up in the fetal position
just trying to stay alive.
>> Ah!
>> Look at you.
See, that's why you impress me
so much, for a scrawny little
kid.
I love meeting the favorites.
I wish I was on their tribe.
Cirie, Ami, now Ozzy.
I'm learning from you guys.
You know, so each time I'm
learning something, which I
appreciate and I pick up and I
try to use..
>> Open coconuts, boil water,
make fire.
>> I mean, being here with you
guys is cool, but being here is
not cool.
I don't care about the immunity
idol.
I mean, I did that, done that,
been there.
I don't feel like doing it no
more.
>> Let's get some clams, because
I'm hungry.
>> All right.
>> I'm going to go look.
KB, my partner from the Airai
Tribe, is so dishearted that
she doesn't even want to look
for the idol.
So I told her I'm just going to
go look for some food, and she
is, hopefully, making a fire.
I don't know if I'm going to
find the idol today, but at
least I'll get a little bit
closer.
I've already found two clues, so
I'm on a little bit of a roll.
There's not that much sunlight
left, and I want to see if I can
find it before the sun goes
down.
If I can find the idol, that
would make things so much
easier.
There's a lot of guys out there
that want to beat me.
It's really key that I find the
idol.
"Look in a place where you made
your arrival"-- "where you made
your arrival."
I can kind of relax a little
bit.
Now it's just a question of
being sly enough to put it back
in my hat, sneak it back in my
bag without her seeing.
A big piece of wood just, like,
washed up, I think, at night.
>> Are you talking about that
big, long piece that's over
there?
>> Yeah.
That's a nice piece.
>> Yeah, I moved that up.
We had a little fire, and then
it went out.
>> It'll get going.
>> Yeah, pretty much.
Taking a lesson from Yau-Man and
Peih-Gee, I'm just going to try
and fashion some sort of fake
idol.
Just got to make it look
semiprofessional.
>> It's like a spiny starfish.
I don't think so.
>> You didn't see any clams out
here on this side?
>> Um, not really.
>> I'm so tired of eating
coconut, though.
>> Yeah.
This is Igor, the immunity idol,
the fake immunity idol.
God, I hope someone finds it and
tries to play it.
I think, if I wrap it up in that
cloth that I found it in and
hide it in the exact same place,
that it's worth a shot.
I think it'll work, at least for
some time, throw people off the
trail a little bit.
Hopefully it can do some good or
some bad.
Do your job now, buddy.
( rooster crowing )
>> Hey, Charlie.
Anybody you'd like me to call,
Charlie, give them your last
good-byes?
Go in peace-- or pieces.
( laughter )
>> Good morning, Gloria.
Charlie, I think you might be
headed for the slaughterhouse
today.
If we don't win today, I might
be headed for the slaughterhouse
too, so I know how you're
feeling, buddy.
>> I don't know.
I really haven't made up my
mind.
>> I'm telling you that I would
be loyal to you to the end, and
I don't think Jonathan could
make that promise.
>> Jonathan will make that
promise, and he won't keep it.
>> Well, but he's a liar, and
you know that better than
anyone.
I love that Jonathan's pissing
people off, and also he's
somebody who they know they
can't trust, so I'm hoping that
they realize that he's a much
more dangerous person to keep
around because of the ease with
which he would flip.
>> You make a very valid point,
I think.
>> He's a charmer.
He's an actor.
>> Well, you just came... like,
you came off guns blazing right
out of the gates.
>> Eliza and Parvati were
talking, and I overtook them.
All I heard was "Get rid of
Jonathan.
He really doesn't like you.
He's told me that he wants
to..."
She'll say anything she needs to
say, and it's so painful to
watch somebody on the outside
who's trying to get back on the
inside.
I totally understand.
I feel sorry for her.
>> He followed us on purpose.
>> He gets so paranoid.
>> Kind of.
>> Eliza's just trying to stay
in the game, you know?
She's trying to save her butt
now.
So she's kind of selling
Jonathan, like, throwing him
under the bus.
And I'd say if we went to tribal
tonight, Eliza would be going
home.
So yeah, she should be saying
anything she can to save herself
right now.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Ozzy and
Kathy, returning from Exile
Island.
>> You all right?
>> It was long, longer than I
thought.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, I'm guessing
Exile wasn't so much tough as it
was an opportunity to get a clue
to the idol, maybe get an idea
where it might be.
>> I guess I was just thinking
all the clues are going to be in
the same place and maybe it
would be as easy as just digging
a hole or something.
But it's a lot harder than I
thought it was going to be.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Erik, give up the immunity idol.
Thanks.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
On my go, six tribe members will
race to a large six-point
sliding hub, which is secured to
a stand using six locks.
Each player must find the one
key that works for their lock.
You must then maneuver through
the forest by shifting, sliding,
and adjusting each other,
collecting money bead necklaces
along the way.
Once you've collected all six
necklaces, the two remaining
tribe members will take the six
necklaces and place them on the
decoding wheel.
If the necklaces are arranged
correctly, the letters that
correspond with the tribe-
colored beads will combine to
form a three-word phrase.
The first tribe to get it right
wins immunity, safe another day.
Losing tribe, tribal council,
another person will be voted
out.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Fans, you have one
extra member, sitting out.
You cannot sit out the same
person in back-to-back
challenges.
Chet sat out in the last
challenge.
Who's it going to be?
>> Tracy.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Tracy going to sit
this one out.
Tracy, take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategy, we'll get
started.
All right, here we go.
Solving the puzzle for the fans,
Chet and Kathy-- for the
favorites, Cirie and Eliza.
For immunity, survivors ready.
Go!
>> Come on, guys.
>> There you go, guys.
>> Oh, careful!
>> PROBST: All six tribe members
got to get in the harness before
you start unlocking.
It going to take teamwork to win
this challenge.
>> In.
>> I'm in.
>> PROBST: Favorites are in.
Start unlocking.
>> Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Ozzy has his undone.
Passes over to James.
Fans are in.
Start unlocking.
>> You got it, Erik.
>> PROBST: There are six keys.
One key fits one lock.
A little bit of luck involved
finding the right key.
James has his undone.
Parvati now working on her lock.
>> Come on, Parv.
>> You got to pull it, bro.
>> PROBST: Erik can't find the
key, passes off to Natalie.
Going to have to come back to
Erik.
Parvati has hers open.
Ami now working on her lock.
>> Take your time.
>> PROBST: Favorites are halfway
there.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Natalie opens her
lock.
>> Good job, Nat.
>> PROBST: Joel now working on
his.
>> You got it, Ami.
>> PROBST: Ami has her lock
undone.
Penner now working on his.
Joel has his lock.
Jason now working on his lock.
>> Go, Jason.
>> That's it, that's it.
Pass it off.
>> PROBST: Penner has his open.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Favorites down to one
lock.
Once Amanda is open, they're
free.
>> Come on, Amanda.
>> PROBST: Amanda quickly gets
hers.
>> Okay, let's go.
>> Good job, guys!
Good job!
>> PROBST: Favorites, all
unlocked, headed onto the
course.
>> Come on, guys!
Don't give up!
>> Come on, man!
>> PROBST: Favorites doing a
good job right away of figuring
out how to maneuver in the
sliding hub.
Jason has his open.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Alexis now working.
>> Let's go, Alexis!
>> Through the middle.
Through the middle.
>> PROBST: Favorites are out on
the course with a big lead.
>> Ami, want to get the first
necklace?
>> Yeah, I got one.
>> PROBST: Ami has the first
necklace for the favorites.
Alexis has her lock open.
Favorites making quick work of
this course.
Fans falling further behind,
still working on their locks.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: They are not out of
the gate yet.
>> Okay, got it.
>> PROBST: Parvati grabs the
third necklace for the
favorites.
>> Let Amanda come through.
>> Go, Amanda.
>> Are you through?
>> You got it?
>> PROBST: Amanda has a necklace
for the favorites.
They're down to two necklaces
left.
>> It's okay, guys.
Everyone take a deep breath.
>> PROBST: Erik finally gets his
lock open.
Fans have a lot of ground to
make up.
>> Careful, careful, careful.
>> Lift up and push the rope.
>> Let Ozzy come through.
>> PROBST: Ozzy has a necklace
for the favorites.
>> Wait, wait, wait.
Go around that side.
>> I can't, y'all.
>> PROBST: Fans having trouble
making any sense of this course
and how to work with the hub.
>> Yes!
One more, one more, guys!
>> PROBST: One necklace left for
the favorites.
James reaches for it and has it.
Favorites are heading back now
with all six necklaces.
>> You guys go through the
middle.
>> Hey, hey, hey!
Ow, ow!
You're going to break my legs.
One second, one second.
I can't move.
I have no where to go.
>> PROBST: Fans just now out on
the course.
>> I have one.
Should I get it?
>> PROBST: Erik has a necklace
for the fans.
>> James, go back as far as you
can.
>> PROBST: Experience clearly
paying off for the favorites--
not even close.
>> Ozzy come all the way this
way.
Hurry up.
Get on the mat.
>> We're on the mat.
We're on the mat.
>> PROBST: Favorites are back.
Go!
Give up those necklaces.
>> Go, baby, go.
>> PROBST: Eliza, Cirie, start
working on that puzzle.
You got to match up the tribe-
colored beads with the correct
letter.
>> Natalie, move forward, move
forward.
>> PROBST: Mikey B. has a
necklace for the fans.
>> R-i-b-e.
We need a purple one right here.
>> Ready?
Purple right here.
>> Turn, turn, turn.
>> "Tribe."
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Eliza, Cirie with a
big lead working on this puzzle.
>> S-t-a-y.
>> "Stay."
>> "Tribe stay."
>> "Stays," it's going to be
"stays."
>> I got this one.
>> PROBST: Natalie has a
necklace for the fans.
Fans now have three of their
necklaces.
>> Come on, guys.
You're still in it.
>> Okay, rotate.
>> PROBST: Fans three necklaces
short of getting back.
>> You guys got this.
>> "In."
>> PROBST: Eliza and Cirie think
they may have it.
Jason has a necklace for the
fans.
They're down to two necklaces
left.
>> "Intact."
Wait a minute.
>> Oh, my God.
>> "Intact."
Is it "i-n-t-a-c-t"?
See if this fits.
>> PROBST: Eliza and Cirie think
they have it right.
>> "Tribe stays intact."
>> PROBST: "Tribe stays intact"
is right.
Favorites win immunity!
( cheering )
>> I love you guys!
I love you guys!
Good job!
>> PROBST: Favorites,
congratulations.
( applause )
Immunity, no tribal council
tonight, nobody going home.
Fans, different story.
We do have tribal council
tonight.
Somebody is going home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Favorites, you guys can head
out.
( cheering )
>> The crew of misfits which is
Airai lost again, not even close
again.
Yeah, yeah, we got some talent.
I don't know what Joel has up
his sleeve.
He backstabbed me early in the
game and voted off Mary.
So my goal is to pretend that
I'm Joel's ally and that I
forgive him, vote Chet out.
I'll keep Joel around as long as
I can, until right before the
merge, and then cut his damn
head off.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, my mind is just
spinning just the fact that he's
still here, you know?
And so he is the weakest.
He is the weakest.
And if we get rid of him, then
that'll make me feel secure
about your position to me.
>> Sure.
>> Where you're still in control
of the game, but you're not
dominating the game, you know,
as far as my position.
>> No, I hear you, but I'd
rather have Kathy out.
>> Yeah.
>> But I hear you.
>> But, you know, just food for
thought.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Seriously.
>> Who's us?
>> You all right, buddy?
>> No.
>> Yeah, you are.
>> Things are very crazy.
I think it's very possible that
Chet could go home tonight.
I think Chet could go home just
like that.
So if Chet's gone, that's one of
my votes, and then Kathy, that's
two, and then I'll be next.
>> My mind is in the game.
My head is in the game.
My body is out of the game, and
it's not by my choice.
>> You know, we need to stick
together.
Let's take it to the next level.
Let's try to stir it up.
I may not have a lot of power
here in this tribe, but I can
tell you this much: I'm going to
go down with a fight.
Why not?
>> What's up?
>> Yo.
>> I'm going to help with wood.
>> So truthfully, who are y'all
voting for?
>> Chet and Kathy.
>> That'll happen.
Just... it can't happen right
now, I don't think.
We need his strength right now
to win challenges.
Basically, Mikey and Jason feel
that Chet is weak, rundown, and
the rest of them, I'm not... I
think they're going to do
whatever Mikey asks them to do.
>> Why are you letting him call
the shots right now?
I don't understand that.
>> I don't know.
Am I letting him?
I don't know.
>> Yes, you are.
>> Yeah, you're letting him.
>> You think so?
>> Absolutely, dude.
You're rolling over.
You are.
I mean, it's crazy.
You said you were going to get
Mike off a long time ago.
Here's your opportunity.
I don't understand what... I'm
angry with you about it.
I'm going to be honest with you.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, you're freaking just
following, like...
>> No, I think...
>> Like a herd of cattle down
the road.
>> I am threatened by Mikey.
That's why I wanted to get Mary
out so early, because of the two
of them together.
And maybe I should have gone
with Mikey on the first vote
versus Mary.
>> Oh, yeah.
Oh, he took that very personal.
And that's why I know that I've
got a target on my back from
him.
>> Mike's going to take you down
the next chance he gets because
of what you did to Mary.
>> I think he will, absolutely.
>> Okay, so this is his next
chance.
Just be aware of that.
>> And you know what?
>> Well, what are you hearing?
Why are you saying that?
What are you hearing?
>> I'm just very intuitive, and
I know a lot of stuff just
because I do, because I'm born
with it.
And I'm not saying that I'm some
type of guru or anything like
that.
>> No, no.
>> It's just that the writing is
on the wall, seriously.
All you need is one person, and
we can take Mike down.
>> Uh-huh.
>> If one of us is gone, you're
done.
We can't help you anymore.
We can't.
We can't do anything.
But with five, we can do
something.
>> So you guys are wanting to
vote Mikey.
>> Yes.
>> We'll see.
Tonight will be interesting.
>> Personally, I think it's
going to go me tonight.
That's what I'm thinking.
>> And that would mean that Joel
did the wrong thing.
>> Whatever.
>> PROBST: Sorry to see you guys
here.
After tonight's vote, you'll be
even with the favorites.
So, Jason, that might imply that
the game is even.
Do you think it is?
>> Right now, I would definitely
say that the favorites have an
advantage.
We've lost four of the past six
challenges.
But you know, maybe tonight's
tribal council will be able to
make a stronger tribe.
>> PROBST: Joel, how important
is it to keep a tribe strong in
terms of winning challenges?
>> It's extremely important.
You know, the weaker our
individuals are, the weaker we
are as a team.
>> PROBST: Who here will own up
to the fact that maybe they
haven't delivered that well in
challenges?
Chet, what's been lacking?
>> For me, probably maybe the
first challenge I did in the
water was a little bit more than
what I thought it was.
But when it comes to certain
challenges, I can take certain
roles where I wouldn't need that
extreme strength.
>> PROBST: So other than that
challenge, you feel pretty good
about your effort?
>> Yes, I do.
>> To be honest with you, Chet
has been hurting.
I mean, Chet's been exhausted
for four days straight.
It's nothing personal against
him.
I just don't think he has the
physical capacity to compete.
>> Can I say something?
I didn't compete, and Chet
didn't compete, and Kathy didn't
compete, and they still lost.
So tell me how you can take
blame for that.
>> PROBST: Mikey B., in a
perfect world, what happens when
you go back to camp tonight?
>> I just want to vote out the
people who are weak and who are
physically unable to perform.
And I hope people who told me
the way they were voting tonight
stick to it, because sometimes
you have to give a little trust
to earn a little trust.
>> PROBST: Erik, there seems to
be somewhat of a consensus that
we need to keep the tribe
physically strong for
challenges.
Do you agree with that?
>> I agree we need to keep this
tribe strong, but it's not about
physical attributes in all these
challenges.
I think that there's more to it
than that.
>> PROBST: Joel, you were almost
nodding in agreement.
>> I think strength is not just
physical strength.
Am I the biggest, strongest guy
on this team?
Yes.
But that doesn't mean that I'm
going to be the number-one
person in every challenge that
we have.
>> Exactly.
My point is really there's a
direct way to go about
something, but that's not the
best way.
I mean, you can run into a wall
100 times; that's not the best
way to get rid of a wall.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Jason.
>> Again I need to emphasize the
importance of tonight's vote in
determining our future as a
tribe.
We have lost four of six
challenges.
So take a moment to really think
about how important it is who we
keep on the island and who we
let go.
>> PROBST: Any other comments
from anybody else?
All right.
Now it is time to vote.
Jason, you're up.
>> Please leave the island.
>> Mike, you've been a loud
mouth from day one, and you
never seem to learn.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now is the time to do
so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Chet.
Chet.
Two votes Chet.
Mike.
One vote Mike.
Two votes Chet.
Mike.
We're tied: two votes Mike, two
votes Chet.
Chet.
That's three votes Chet, two
votes Mike.
Mike.
We're tied: three votes Mike,
three votes Chet.
Mike.
That's four votes Mike, three
votes Chet.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites,
Mike.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Mike, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, tonight's vote was
obviously a very big vote.
Whether or not you made the
right decision, only time will
tell.
Grab your torches.
Back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
Drop your buffs.
We are switching tribes.
...the fans mix with the
favorites, and a physical
challenge puts some survivors in
jeopardy.
>> I mean, if you went back to
medieval times, I think we'd
kill him ourselves.
>> Ow!
Damn it!
>> Apparently, he could lose his
leg.
>> I'm not surprised it's me.
No, because I'm playing with a
bunch of weak players who
listened to Joel.
Don't trust Joel.
He's going to stab you in the
back.
It was obvious who needed to go.
I wish I was in the game longer.
I guess I came out too strong.
But I was never lazy.
I always did what I could to
help the tribe.
So yeah, they're going to miss
me, no doubt.