>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor, as the game reaches
its final days...
>> What is the plan?
>> Final five girls.
>> PROBST: ...a powerful
alliance of women has taken
control.
>> It's the black widow brigade.
We're spinning the guys around
as much as we can, and then
we're devouring them.
>> PROBST: In their first move,
Parvati and Cirie organized the
betrayal of their longtime ally
Ozzy.
Ozzy, the tribe has spoken.
>> The plan is in play.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: Then Natalie
spearheaded a second double-
cross.
>> It would be brilliant for
Jason to go out just like Ozzy,
blindsided, flossing my teeth
with his jugular.
>> PROBST: 11th person voted out
of Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites,
Jason.
When Jason left, he was the
second person in a row to be
voted out while holding the
hidden immunity idol.
James and Erik are now the only
men left.
Anybody who still feels safe is
a fool.
James, on your way out, I want
medical to look at your finger.
>> It was no big deal, just
a little clam cut, whatever,
nothing really to bother with.
We got to tribal, and it was
kind of swelling up a little
bit, you know.
So I just had medical look at it
and make sure everything is good
and give me a little
antibacterial, and I'll be all
right.
>> Okay, I'm just going to stick
this in, okay?
So we can't let this go very
long.
>> How many days do I have?
>> Till tomorrow morning, when
we come back out and look at
this, okay?
>> I work with my hands.
It's very important that I get
this thing fixed as soon as
possible, because I need my
hands when I get back home.
>> That infection that's in your
finger here has probably gone
into the joint.
If, in the morning, this doesn't
look good, then it needs to go
to surgery.
( theme song playing )
>> Okay, so, James, now,
reiterate.
>> I don't know.
>> What do you mean, you're out
of the game?
>> No.
>> Obviously not.
>> Yeah.
>> James hurt his finger.
He got it looked at.
And I guess the infection is
really, really close to the
joint, which can lead to
permanent problems.
Oh, my God, James.
>> It's going to be all right.
>> I hope his finger gets
better, and I hope that they
come tomorrow morning and say,
"Hey, you're fine," you know,
like, "you can finish the game."
( snoring )
>> I was just walking in the
middle of the night with no
light, and I just ate it,
really, really bad-- like, the
worst fall I've ever had.
And I hurt my knee.
>> How's the leg, Lexi?
>> Sore.
>> Alexis takes a tumble in the
dark.
James, he has his finger
infected.
I know this is bad because I am
a nurse, but... that's two less
people I have to fight against
for a million dollars.
>> This is just so sore.
>> It's puffy.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
>> Look at our statues.
>> Look at me!
Are you kidding?
>> Look at Parvati.
>> Look at my bathing suit.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: You like seeing your
likeness?
>> That's really funny.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you're each going to
answer a series of questions
about your tribe mates in
private.
I'll tally the results.
I'm then going to ask you those
same questions, only this time
you're trying to guess whose
name came up the most often from
the group.
Each time you answer correctly,
you get to chop one rope of
another tribe member.
When you've chop three ropes,
they're out of the game.
>> Oh, no!
>> PROBST: Last person left
standing wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes.
>> Sure.
>> PROBST: 30 days is a long
time to be away from home.
Time for a little love.
Parvati, here's your mom, Gail.
Come on out, Gail!
>> You look so good.
>> You look awesome.
You smell fabulous.
>> PROBST: Erik, here's your
brother, Curt.
>> No way!
>> PROBST: Come on, curt!
>> Curt!
>> You look so funny.
>> I know.
I got beard!
I got a beard!
Look at this!
>> Sweet beard.
I love it.
>> That's Jeff Probst!
That's Jeff Probst!
He's just standing there.
>> PROBST: Erik, you're a freak.
Natalie, you know who's here to
see you?
It's your mom, Rocky.
Come on out, Rocky!
>> Sorry I stink so bad.
>> You don't.
>> Look at my armpit hair.
( laughter )
>> PROBST: All right, Alexis,
here's your brother, Nathan.
Come on out, Nathan!
>> You doing all right?
Look at you.
>> I don't want to let go.
>> PROBST: Amanda, you ready for
some love?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Here's your sister.
>> I need a little love.
>> PROBST: Katrina.
>> Oh.
>> Hello, jungle chicken.
You smell better.
>> I do?
>> Than last time.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: James Sr., come on
out.
( applause )
>> All dressed up.
>> What's up, Dad?
>> You look good!
I wish I looked like that.
>> PROBST: Cirie.
>> Come on, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Let's bring out your
man.
HB, come on out!
( applause )
Cirie's husband.
>> Oh!
>> I brought you this.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: The winner of today's
challenge, with their loved one,
will go to Jellyfish Lake, where
you will swim with literally
thousands of non-stinging
jellyfish.
It is truly a one-of-a-kind
experience.
In addition, Exile Island is
back in play again.
A new idol has been hidden.
First clue is out there.
Somebody's going.
Survivors, give you a minute to
fill out your survey.
We'll get started.
You guys ready to get to it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You're now trying to
guess whose name came up the
most often, even if that's
different from what you might
have written down individually.
First question, who does the
most for the tribe?
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Everybody reveal.
Everybody says James, except
James.
Correct answer is James.
Everybody got it right...
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: ...except the guy who
does the most for the tribe.
All right, Cirie, you're up.
Cirie heading over to Amanda.
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: Amanda takes her
first hit.
>> Natalie, take your swing.
>> No!
>> PROBST: Erik takes his first
hit.
>> Ow.
>> PROBST: Conveniently, Erik is
next up.
Payback is tough.
Alexis gives James his first
hit.
>> Ooh, I'm going to fix you.
>> PROBST: Parvati gives James
his second hit.
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: Last but not least,
Amanda, who gives Parvati her
first hit.
>> PROBST: Everybody took a hit,
except Cirie and Alexis.
Next question, who never shuts
up?
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer is Parvati.
>> I knew it.
>> PROBST: Amanda, James,
Alexis, and Erik got it right.
Erik, you're up.
Take your hit.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Alexis goes for
payback.
James goes for Alexis.
>> Oh!
>> Cirie, I have to get even.
( sighs )
>> PROBST: Amanda gives Cirie
her first hit.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Erik, Alexis, and
James with only one rope left.
Next question, who mistakenly
thinks they are in control of
this game?
Everybody reveal.
Everybody said Parvati, except
for Parvati and Alexis.
Correct answer is Parvati.
James, you're up.
>> This one.
>> PROBST: James gives Parvati
her second hit.
Amanda does the same for
Natalie.
Erik heads over to Cirie's
block, gives her her second hit.
Natalie heading to Amanda, gives
her her second hit.
Cirie making her way to
Parvati's block.
Only one rope left.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Wow!
>> That's a little vicious,
Jeff.
( laughter )
>> You're in trouble.
>> PROBST: Parvati is the first
person out of this game.
Next question, who is the most
honest?
Everybody reveal.
Wow, all over the board.
Correct answer is Alexis.
The only person who got it right
was Cirie.
Take a shot.
Cirie heads right over to Erik.
>> After I didn't chop you.
>> Oh, my God!
Your hair fell off!
>> My hair flew off.
>> PROBST: We are down to five.
Everybody down to one rope left.
Next question, who are you least
likely to invite to a family
dinner?
Everybody reveal.
James is the correct answer.
>> What's up with that?
>> PROBST: Everybody got it
right, except Natalie.
Alexis, you're up.
Whoever you hit, you're knocking
them out of this game.
Alexis...
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: ...obliterates James.
James is out of the challenge
and cannot win, but James still
gets to knock somebody else out.
>> No!
James, I didn't even hit you!
>> Oh!
>> It's so violent!
I can't get over it!
>> PROBST: Amanda, you're up.
Take your hit.
Who are you going to knock out
of the game?
Natalie is out of the challenge.
Cirie, you're out of the
challenge.
You have one hit left.
And in doing so, you are going
to decide who wins this
challenge, Amanda or Alexis.
Cirie heads right over to
Amanda.
>> Sorry.
>> PROBST: Alexis wins reward.
Nate, come on over, join your
sis.
( applause )
Nathan and Alexis going on
reward together.
You're going to choose two
people to come with you, along
with their loved ones.
Pick your first person.
>> I'm picking Cirie.
>> PROBST: Cirie and her
husband, HB, going to be joining
you.
One more survivor.
Who's going?
>> Nat.
>> PROBST: Natalie.
Rocky, that means you are going
to be going to Jellyfish Lake as
well.
All right, Alexis, you have one
other big decision to make.
Who are you sending to Exile?
>> Amanda.
>> PROBST: Amanda, get your
stuff, head out.
Boat's waiting on you.
>> Can I give my sister a hug
good-bye?
>> PROBST: Nope.
I'm sorry.
>> Love you.
Bye, you guys.
>> PROBST: All right, loved
ones, Gail, James, Curt,
Katrina, time for you guys to
go.
Head back the way you came.
>> I'm doing good, dude.
>> Bye, Dad.
>> I'm doing great.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: All right, James,
Erik, Parvati, head back to
camp.
James on your way out, I want
medical to look at your finger.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: All right, enjoy.
>> All right, thanks!
>> PROBST: Have fun.
Head out.
>> How is it faring?
>> All right.
So hopefully it'll be cool.
She might look at it now and be
like, "Hey, it's not that bad."
So hopefully she'll let me stay
and we'll be able to just keep
things rolling, hopefully.
>> Have you got any pain going
into your hand?
>> No, not at all.
>> Any going into the rest of
your finger?
>> No.
It hurts on the sides.
>> That's where it's sore?
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Okay.
The big risk with this is that
it goes into that joint.
Bugs that get in there infect
the joint really quickly.
It's not superficial.
It's deep.
>> PROBST: So, Carolyn, catch
me up.
What's the status?
>> The risk of leaving him out
here, obviously, is that the
infection's going to set in.
It's a dirty environment.
It's dangerous potentially for
him-- for not just his finger,
but his whole hand.
>> PROBST: So, James, you know
the way the game works.
It's always your call, unless
medical decides it's too big a
risk.
So, Carolyn, are you saying it
is too big a risk?
Are you pulling him from the
game?
What's the call?
>> If he'd had absolutely no
pain and it was just
superficial, then I'd be happy.
But my call is that it is too
big a risk.
It is.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
you out of here and get you to a
hospital.
>> Cool.
>> PROBST: Thanks, Carolyn.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Most of your tribe is
on a reward, but those that are
here, you want to say good-bye?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right.
>> I mean, I'd much rather have
been voted out, but I'm
definitely ready to go and get
this thing fixed.
Ain't no need playing with it.
Ain't no need to fraternize
about it.
Just go and get it done.
>> Get out.
>> Yeah.
>> No.
>> You're leaving?
>> Yeah.
>> James!
>> No way!
>> James is, like, one of the
toughest guys I've ever met in
my life, and I just have so much
respect for James and who he is
as a person.
It just... it's just not fair,
you know?
It's just not right for him to
go out like that.
>> Good-bye.
All right, man.
>> Go drink some beers.
It'll be fine.
>> It's going to be so lonely
without him.
>> I know.
I'm the only man left.
>> Alexis won the challenge, and
we got to take our loved ones.
Never in a million years did you
ever think you'd do this, huh?
And we got to hike up this
little path and go swim with
stingless jellyfish.
>> You see it?
>> It's right here.
>> No wonder I felt something
touching me.
>> Ah, I see one.
Look, it's in my hand.
I see more.
>> It was so magnificent to see
nature like that.
I think it might have been a
breakthrough for me to swim with
the jellyfish, because it kind
of, like, opened my eyes a
little bit.
Like, everything is not a
threat.
Maybe it's changed me a little
bit as to being afraid of every
little thing.
>> Man, there's a million of
them!
>> They are everywhere.
>> Golly!
>> Never before have I ever seen
anything like this.
>> Incredible!
>> Clue number one, "Underneath
where the waves lap, you'll find
another piece of the map.
Closer than you think, you'll
find the next link."
I just arrived at Exile, and now
that I'm here, my only priority
while I'm here is getting the
idol.
The waves lap right there.
"Now go back to the top and look
out to sea.
It's not in the mouth where you
think it might be.
But halfway there, you'll find
it submerged."
I just found the third clue.
It pretty much says I have to
align the smallest island with
the hut, and it makes a line.
So I'm digging a line from the
tower that's still in line with
the island.
Hopefully I'm on the right
track.
If not, I'm going to be doing a
lot of digging for no reason.
Come on!
Oh, my God!
( laughing )
I thought I was going to be
digging for the rest of my life.
"Hidden immunity idol is
buried"-- oh, my God-- "back at
your tribe's camp, underneath
your tribe's flag."
Oh, my God!
>> Hey!
Yeah, Erik's in the cave.
He got medically taken out.
>> They took James?
>> Are you kidding me?
>> Oh, my God, such a huge shock
to come back from camp after
that family members' reward and
being, like, so high and hearing
that James has been kicked out
for medical reasons.
It's very terrifying the idea
that I would be sent home
because my knee is injured.
>> I started bawling, crying.
I was, like, so emotional.
And it was just me and Erik.
It's been me and Erik all day.
And with James leaving the game,
it kind of puts us in a weird
space, because we absolutely
have to beat Erik at the next
immunity challenge.
If it comes down to him winning
immunity, the women will
definitely have to start eating
each other.
>> We're down to six people now?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, it's us and Erik.
>> So we need to figure out what
we need to do.
>> How you feeling this morning?
>> It's bad, you know?
>> Shaky?
>> Yeah.
Like, I have no stability in it.
>> Right.
>> Do you really feel like you
can do this for seven more days?
>> Yeah.
>> You do?
It's not even a question.
>> So you don't want us to vote
you out?
>> It's not even an option.
>> Because it just looks like
you're in excruciating pain.
>> But I can deal with that, you
know?
>> Okay.
>> This morning, Parvati said,
"Listen, girl, like, we can vote
you out and, you know, you can
go home and, like, have medical
attention."
But, I mean, there's definitely
something that was a little
threatening, so I hope that it's
not a reflection of her
mentality for the rest of the
game.
But then again, you never know.
But what do y'all see?
Like, what were y'all thinking?
>> Erik goes next.
I think it depends on who wins
immunity and what happens.
Like, what do y'all think?
>> If I were to put myself in
the final three, I couldn't win
against Amanda.
Like, she's played a good social
game where everybody is on her
side, and that's where the
problem is.
>> It's been pretty much me and
her since day one, so I feel
like I can't screw her over at
this point.
>> Right.
>> So if something were to
happen, as far as her getting
voted, like, I can't have a part
in it.
>> Yeah, you can't write her
name down.
>> Like, I just won't.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Amanda,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Oh!
>> Where's James?
>> He got medically taken out.
>> He got taken out after the
challenge.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Game continues.
We are down to six, having three
people leave this game due to
reasons other than being voted
out-- definitely a Survivor
first.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Erik, I'll take back the
necklace.
>> Here you go.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
each going to take turns firing
a high-powered rifle, attempting
to break colored sake bottles.
The first person to break all
three of their sake bottles wins
immunity, is guaranteed a one-
in-five shot at winning this
game.
All right, we'll draw for order,
and we'll get started.
Here we go.
First round, Natalie, you're up.
>> Let's go, Nat.
>> Go, mama.
>> PROBST: You are aiming for
one of your three colored sake
bottles.
Looking for a purple sake
bottle.
Get on the board early.
Natalie connects, breaks her
first bottle.
Natalie on the board with one.
>> Nice shot!
>> PROBST: Good first shot.
Amanda.
Amanda looking to hit a light-
blue bottle.
Misses to the right.
Parvati.
Parvati looking to nail that
middle yellow bottle.
Parvati connects!
Parvati on the board with her
first bottle.
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: Natalie and Parvati
both with one.
Cirie looking to hit a white
sake bottle with her name on it.
>> Damn.
>> PROBST: Cirie misses high and
wide to the right.
Erik looking for a red sake
bottle.
Got three to choose from.
Erik with his first bottle.
>> Good job, Erik.
>> PROBST: Alexis is up.
Alexis looking for green.
Just misses.
At the end of the first round,
Natalie, Parvati, and Erik each
have one bottle.
Natalie, you're up.
Natalie could go back out in the
lead with this shot.
>> Get them, mama.
>> Oh!
>> Off the back.
>> Ricocheted, ricocheted.
>> PROBST: Amanda looking for a
light-blue target.
>> Crap!
>> PROBST: Almost hits Alexis's
bottle.
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: Parvati just misses.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Nicked the name tag.
>> PROBST: Erik connects again!
Erik with his second bottle.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Erik now in the lead.
>> PROBST: Alexis, no luck.
Erik in the lead with two.
Natalie and Parvati both with
one.
Natalie, you're up.
Natalie needs another hit to tie
with Erik.
>> Nice.
( applause )
>> PROBST: Natalie connects,
hitting her second bottle.
Natalie and Erik each have two
bottles.
Amanda connects.
Amanda on the board with her
first bottle.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Parvati misses again.
Just misses.
>> Close.
>> PROBST: Here's where we
stand.
Natalie has two.
Erik has two.
Erik has not yet taken his shot
in this round.
Erik, you're up.
If you hit your third bottle,
you win immunity.
Erik can close it out here.
Takes his aim.
Erik does it.
Erik wins immunity!
>> Wow.
Good job, Erik.
>> Good job, Erik.
( applause )
>> PROBST: Erik, once again
immunity is yours.
Erik is safe at tonight's vote.
One of you five women going home
tonight.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
Head back to camp.
See you at tribal.
>> Okay, first of all, I want
you guys to know that I don't
have it, so I'm going to empty
my bag.
>> How many clues did you get?
>> Because I don't have it.
I could not find the third clue
for the life of me.
I couldn't find it.
It was submerged under the
water, and the current was so
strong I couldn't... I couldn't
find it.
>> So the clue was in the water?
>> Yeah, it was underwater.
>> That's frustrating.
I'm sorry, girl.
>> That's all right.
But I wanted to find it, you
know?
>> That's okay.
It's cursed anyway.
>> Yeah, that's legit, man.
>> It was harder than I thought,
obviously.
>> The chicken?
>> He's biting the dust.
You want to say bye?
>> Time to go.
>> Should I kill it now?
Do you guys want to kill it now?
>> I kind of want to do it.
>> You want to do it?
>> Killing chicken!
>> Oh, slick.
Okay.
>> What do you think is the best
move for us.
>> I think Alexis.
>> I think Natalie.
>> I really think Alexis.
>> I think Alexis is our biggest
threat as far as jury votes in
the end, and I'm looking towards
the end of this game right now.
I see where Amanda is coming
from, on the other hand, as far
as Natalie being the bigger
threat in challenges.
So it's kind of a toss-up right
now.
And I think that you could
get...
They want to.
>> They do?
>> They've been talking about it
while you're gone.
>> You really don't think that
you could, like, hold it over
his head that you kept him here
longer than Ami?
>> That's what I was thinking.
>> Find that damn idol, lady.
>> I think Amanda would do
really well in the final three--
really well.
>> Amanda is, hands down, the
biggest jury threat.
And so it's like... it's not
even fun to battle it out to get
to the final three to just...
>> Lose to her.
>> ...lose to her.
And if we have an opportunity to
take her out now...
>> Luckily she doesn't have the
idol.
>> Yeah.
>> So that's the good thing.
>> At this point, I know I'm
between you and Parv.
That's where I'm at.
>> To vote for me or Parv?
>> Yeah.
I feel like you guys are big
threats.
You know?
And, like, when you needed my
help, I helped you out.
>> I feel like you could beat me
in a challenge coming up.
I honestly do.
>> But I helped you out, and I
knew that you were a threat.
>> Okay.
>> Here we go.
Do you know how to carve up a
chicken?
>> Yeah.
>> You on board?
>> I was going to ask you.
So what's the deal?
>> That's the deal.
>> Okay.
>> And it makes sense, I think.
Yeah, I'm on board.
>> Okay.
>> I'm going to be so sorry to
see Amanda go.
But strategically, it's not such
a bad thing, because I don't
think Parvati or myself could
beat her with jury votes.
So it saddens me that it's going
to be Amanda, but it's the game,
you know?
The game must go on.
I want Alexis to go, but Erik is
not...
If I make it even, Amanda, then
we're going to have to vote
again.
If nobody changes their vote,
then all of us pick a rock, and
whoever gets the colored rock,
goes home.
That's how it is at this point.
At the four, then you do a
challenge.
I'm, like, in between a rock and
a hard place.
What do I do?
Make it even and then pick the
rock.
You see my luck.
I couldn't even hit a damn
bottle.
Yeah, yeah.
And it's Erik.
No, you know I didn't want it
like this.
Because now, to me...
You know that I would.
So what do I do, make it a tie?
>> Tender.
>> Well, what happened to
Amanda?
>> No, she's coming.
She just wanted to wash her
armpits because I told her she
stunk.
>> You know, the consensus is me
tonight.
So I'm going to have to see if I
can get the hidden immunity
idol.
And if not, I'm gone.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of the jury, Eliza,
Ozzy, and Jason, voted out at
the last tribal council.
We have one more jury member
slowly making their way to
tribal council.
James making his first
appearance since being pulled
from the game by our medical
team.
All right, jury, first, let me
catch you up.
James was pulled from the game
for a medical injury.
He didn't want to go.
He didn't have a say in it.
Now let's get to the IV bag.
>> I had an infection they had
to take care of.
So that's very bad.
You could lose your hand.
I need my hands to work with, so
it wasn't a chance I was able to
take.
But I'm here now.
As long as I have the IV, I'm
good.
>> PROBST: It's certainly a
first.
Glad you're here.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Okay, Amanda, let's
talk about Exile Island.
Did you spend any time looking
for the hidden immunity idol?
>> It was really windy, and the
currents were really strong, so
I couldn't find it.
It's frustrating when you're
looking for something to save
your life in this game, and I
just didn't do it,
unfortunately.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
threats at this point in the
game.
There's the physical threat.
Then there's the likability
threat.
Cirie, who are the physical
threats at this point in the
game?
Erik and Amanda, pretty much.
>> PROBST: You can't vote for
Erik tonight.
Fingers point to you, Amanda.
>> Yeah, pretty much everyone
here has told me that they're
voting for me tonight.
The only person that's voting
with me tonight is Parvati.
>> Amanda has become like my
little sister in this game.
I can't vote for her, and I
won't.
>> I feel like it's been kind of
me and Erik too.
You know, like, we've gone
through a lot of this together.
And when he needs someone, he
comes across trustworthy.
But then when you need Erik for
something, he finds greener
grasses somewhere else.
That's pretty much how it is.
>> Amanda, directly, I think, is
blaming me for the fact that I
have to make a decision between
who's staying, who's going.
>> But you have to understand.
Like, I helped you stay here
through the merge, and then I
was asking for your help this
time, and you clearly denied me
of that.
And yeah, I'm mad about it.
I'm pretty pissed off right now.
>> PROBST: Natalie, at this
point in the game, who concerns
you the most in terms of "Can't
let them get to the end; they
will win"?
>> Amanda.
She has done no wrong to anyone
sitting over there on the jury,
and voting her out is the
unfortunate part of getting down
to this part of the game.
But I feel the need to at least
be honest with my reasoning
behind my vote.
>> To reiterate what Nat said,
you know, like, we adore her,
and so, like, we're going to
tell her because we respect her
so much.
I would grant that to any of
these people, because I truly
respect every person here right
now.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Erik, you have the individual
immunity necklace.
As always, you can give it to
somebody else if you want.
>> I'm going to keep it.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Erik.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Cirie, you're up.
>> This is only because if I did
not make this vote, I would be
handing you a million dollars.
>> Amanda, I absolutely adore
you.
This is one of the hardest votes
I'll put in.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> It's okay, baby.
>> PROBST: If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
>> About that, Jeff...
I just want to say when I told
you all I didn't have it, I
didn't have it then.
So I didn't lie.
But I got it!
>> PROBST: The rules of Survivor
state that if anybody plays a
hidden immunity idol, any votes
cast against them will not
count, and the person with the
next highest number of votes
will be sent home.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Amanda do not
count.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Amanda-- does not
count.
Amanda-- does not count.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Amanda-- does not
count.
We still have no votes for
anybody.
Alexis.
Alexis, in order to force a tie,
this last vote has to be for
somebody other than you or
Amanda, or you go home.
12th person voted out of
Survivor and the fifth member
of our jury, Alexis.
That's two, and that is enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Alexis, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
You guys are perfecting the art
of the blindside.
That is the good news, and that
is the bad news.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> Every single girl is trying
to talk me into some different
plan, so who do you trust?
Who do you really trust here?
>> I think as we make him feel
confident, he'll do the right
thing.
>> I feel like me, you, and Parv
should go to the end.
>> I could have literally bitch-
slapped him, smack him like his
mother.
>> Yeah, I didn't see that one
coming at all.
But it's a game, so yeah, I'm
not mad at all.
I think I made my papa proud.
I never lied once when I was
here.
I kept the level integrity of
who I am outside of the game.
I'm rooting for my girl Nat, not
even a question.
This is the hardest physical,
mental, spiritual thing I've
ever done, and I'm better for
having been here.