>> JEFF: We are flying over the
beautiful islands of
Micronesia-- crystal-clear
water, magnificent coral reefs,
and one of the most stunning
collections of underwater sea
life in the world.
Just below me are ten Americans
who are about to begin the
adventure of a lifetime.
They share only one thing in
common-- they are all fans of
Survivor.
These fans have finally been
given the chance to be a
contestant in their favorite
game, but they're completely
unaware that they'll be playing
against some of their favorite
Survivors from seasons past.
>> You could be a fan of the
Boston Red Sox, man, but you
don't want to play against the
Boston Red Sox.
You're going to gets your ass
handed to you.
>> I played a perfect game last
time.
I consider myself the greatest
player in the history of the
game.
>> Coming back I'm playing
aggressively, and pretty much no
holds barred for me.
>> The only reason to come back
is for the $1 million.
That's the only reason I will
put up with a lot of suffering
and bugs and smelly people.
>> People at home watching
identify with me.
I'm like the person at home
watching on the coach, remember?
I was the couch potato.
>> I can almost be on the fan's
side.
Because I'm a fan of all these
people.
So for me to see, like, Yau and
Ozzy over here was, like, was
crazy.
>> Everybody wants to beat me
now, and hopefully I can tap
into that same kind of energy
and will that I had last time.
>> JEFF: It is the ultimate game
with a new twist-- ten of
Survivor's biggest fans taking
on ten of their favorite
players.
For the next 39 days, they'll be
forced to work together,
creating a new society, while
battling the elements and each
other.
They must learn to adapt or
they'll be voted out of the
game.
In the end, only one will remain
to claim the million-dollar
prize.
39 days, 20 people, one
Survivor!
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
>> I have always been a huge fan
of Survivor.
When we first pulled in on the
boat, it was a torrential
downpour.
One of my life dreams has been
to come out and try and survive
in the wild, so this is really
incredible for me.
>> JEFF: So welcome to
Micronesia.
>> I'm a fan, so coming
to Survivor and starting up the
game on the beach with Jeff, you
know, seeing him there, it was
surreal.
>> JEFF: You guys want to know
who you're playing against?
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: Seeing how big a fans
of Survivor you are, it is only
fitting that you are going to
compete against some of your
favorite Survivors from seasons
past.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my god!
>> JEFF: Come on out!
Cirie from Exile Island.
>> This is cool for us to eat
this like this, right?
>> JEFF: Come on out!
Ozzy, from Survivor: Cook
Islands.
A little less hair but the same
Ozzy.
>> He's so high up there right
now.
>> I know a lot about Ozzy
simply in terms of competition.
He has owned almost all the
challenges, but I myself am a
track and cross country runner.
I think I have what it takes to
compete at that level.
>> JEFF: Come on out.
Ami from Survivor: Vanautau.
>> Hi, girlfriend.
>> JEFF: Come on out.
Jonathan Penner.
>> Thank you!
>> If you want to mutiny, step
off your mat and join the other
tribe.
>> JEFF: Come on out!
Up next, Eliza from Survivor:
Vanuatu.
>> You've been trying to plot
against me from day one.
>> For the last three freaking
days you have been driving
everybody freaking nuts.
Chill out!
>> JEFF: Come on out!
>> From Survivor: China, James.
>> When I saw James come around
the corner, I got excited,
because he is, up until this
season, the biggest and
strongest that has ever played
the game.
I think I can take him.
>> JEFF: Let's bring out the
next member of your tribe.
Come on out.
Parvati, from Survivor: Cook
Islands.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
I've got two naked guys in a hot
tub.
>> JEFF: Let's see who else is
on this tribe.
Come on out.
Yau-Man from Survivor: Fiji.
>> I'm about to jump out of my
skin here!
Blue turtle.
>> JEFF: The biggest round of
applause so far, Yau-Man.
>> These are people I've watched
on TV, and so there's that
certain awe about them,
especially Yau-Man.
I saw him come out with that
little Yau-Man hat and the
little glasses.
I love the Yau-Man.
>> JEFF: The next member of the
favorites team, Amanda from
Survivor: China.
>> I have a really good idea.
Get rid of James tonight.
He doesn't expect it right now.
>> JEFF: So we have ten fans, we
have nine favorites.
We are one short.
Let's bring out the last member
of the Survivor favorites team,
the most infamous of all
survivors.
Jonny Fairplay, who already
looks intoxicated.
>> My grandmother is not here
for a reason.
She's not around.
>> Love the hat.
Love the hat.
>> JEFF: So, Fairplay, are you
dressing like me?
>> You want to know what you're
playing for?
( laughter )
>> JEFF: I'm actually impressed.
I like to know that you have
aspirations to get out of your
current place in life.
( laughter )
>> Wow.
Good to see you, Jeff.
Always a pleasure.
>> I wanted to throw up when I
saw Jonny Fairplay.
He's a pig.
He's a loser pig.
I would just love one moment to
kick him, one moment to kick
him.
One moment just to kick him hard
in the shin.
>> JEFF: All right, fans, your
tribe name is Airai.
Take a buff and put it on.
Favorites, your tribe name is
Malakal.
Take a buff and put it on.
>> I think the fans versus
favorites setup is the ultimate
challenge.
Because we have the favorites
who obviously have played this
game before, so they're coming
in here with experience, but at
the same time you have us.
And we know their game.
We know not only their strengths
but their weaknesses, too.
And so I think that puts us at a
huge advantage.
>> JEFF: Just across the water
on the other beach, there are
two boats, one for each tribe.
Inside the boat is a map to your
new home.
One other thing-- also across
the beach there are two
individual immunity idols, one
for each tribe.
The first person to find the
idol from each tribe gets the
idol.
These are special idols.
You can only play it the first
time you go to tribal council.
You can go anytime you want.
>> I worked my ass off to get
across that stretch of water.
I beat Ozzy.
And that's good.
That's what I wanted to do.
I needed to show him what I'm
made of.
>> I'm thinking, "You know what?
Take your time, Jonny Fairplay.
Slow and steady wins the race."
I get there, has to be in plain
sight.
It's on the boat.
I grab it.
Well, I grab the one from the
other boat.
Yau-Man tackles my head into the
side of the boat.
>> Sorry!
All these idols seem to like me,
and I hope that there will be
other idols on the way this
season and they will all like
me.
Pick up that!
>> Thanks to Yau-Man, I have
immunity for the very first
tribal council that we go to.
So I'm, like, safe.
>> Trust me, Yau-Man's not
America's hero like you think he
is.
Even Jonny Fairplay wouldn't
tackle someone's head into the
side of a boat for the immunity
idol.
Yau-Man is not nice.
He sucks.
So, as soon as that idol is
gone, see you later, bucko.
>> Here we go!
>> Get out.
Hi, nice to meet you, buddy.
>> Chet, Jason.
When we first pulled up to the
beach it was really exciting.
You know, we are the fans of
Survivor.
So this is all of our dreams to
be out here.
We definitely want to kick the
favorites' ass.
>> We have arrived.
>> As in we have arrived.
>> Arrived, arrived.
>> How about Jonny Fairplay?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm a fan.
I'm not somebody that just said,
"Oh, let's go be on Survivor."
>> Like, they all think they
know how to do it and that,
like, the way they did it was
right.
>> Exactly.
>> Now that we know we're
playing the favorites, I mean,
we are out for blood.
>> We have the advantage,
because we know how they play.
They don't know a damn thing
about us.
>> All right, let's do
something.
our tribe consists of Big Bird.
We've got the southern princess.
We've got the Incredible Hulk.
We've got Jon Bon Jovi in his
prime.
And then we've got Queer Eye for
the Straight Guy.
Man, this is going to be a crew,
let me tell you.
It's on!
>> I think we need to do an
elevated floor.
>> Wherever we build a shelter,
we've got to clear it out.
>> Okay.
>> Do you prefer gay?
I don't even know the right word
to use.
>> You're cool so far.
Go ahead.
I don't get offended, so don't
worry.
>> Is gay okay?
>> That's fine.
Sure.
>> It doesn't mean, like, you
want to be a girl, right?
>> Oh, no, no, heavens no.
>> I knew Chet was a homosexual
right away.
You know, you could just tell he
is.
Yeah, I don't have a problem
with it.
But I've never been friends
with a homosexual.
I think I worked with somebody
in the 1980s bartending that was
gay, but that's been about it.
You know what?
I hope you can be my first gay
man friend.
>> And I absolutely will.
>> Because I never had a gay man
friend.
>> I bet you have and you just
don't know.
>> Maybe.
>> Kathy definitely... she just
kind of puts her foot in her
mouth sometimes.
>> I've never seen implants,
ever.
I've never seen them up close.
>> Who said I have them?
>> She made... she made a
comment about Tracy's boobs.
And I'm like...
>> Oh, my god!
>> The second the crazy lady
found the immunity idol, I think
everyone was a little worried,
because I think we all kind of
felt as a consensus that she was
going to be its first one to go.
>> I'm sure I got off on the
wrong foot.
I guess sometimes it pays to
keep your mouth shut, but I
can't help myself.
>> So here.
Let's build a shelter before it
rains again.
>> The fact that we, the
favorites, have played this game
before, I think that is our
biggest advantage.
And it's an expectation that
we've got to live up to.
>> Can we just make a pact right
now that we're just going to
kick their asses?
>> Of course.
>> We should do our shelter as
fast as possible.
>> It's just out in the open?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, like, do we have
people who know how to build a
shelter?
Let's build a real shelter.
Pretty crazy, fans versus
favorites.
We always knew Jonny Fairplay
was a favorite.
Honestly, I think that's the
smartest place, but, you know,
I'm not fighting anybody on
anything.
The first time around I was just
a single guy on the prowl.
This go-around I've got a
girlfriend at home.
She's seven months pregnant.
Need to bring home some money
for her.
So let's get to work.
I just got a message in a bottle
saying my grandma died, so...
>> Not falling for that one
again.
>> Are you kidding me?
Look at how fast he is.
>> I know, it's insane.
>> I definitely appreciate the
hard work that goes on around
this camp.
It's so much nicer to have
everybody pulling the rope and
getting everything together,
helping each other and stuff.
I almost wanted to give somebody
a hug, because it was really
nice.
>> Nice, Ozzy!
This is so much more pleasant
than day one of last time.
>> I know, right?
>> I mean, we all know what
we're doing already, so, I mean,
the favorites should definitely
have the advantage over the
fans.
>> We're pretty much ready for
palm fronds, right?
>> Yeah.
>> I think we have a good group.
I hope we win.
>> I think so, too.
Everyone's already, like,
bonding together.
I have to win this time.
It's my second time.
I'm not coming back here to
starve and be miserable.
Do you want to get more fronds?
I was the flirt on Cook Islands
and that was it.
Like, there was no other
dimension to me at all, I don't
think.
Do you want a piggyback?
>> Yeah.
>> ( laughing )
Like, outwardly, I'm still going
to be flirty, but I'm playing
smart this time.
Like, I want to make the right
alliances with people that I
know I can trust.
Oh, look at that crab.
( screaming )
And this time there's only one
guy to flirt with, really.
It's the big guy, James.
>> No, don't.
>> He has, like, a pincher on
the bottom.
>> Parvati is definitely
attractive.
And she's... you know, there's
just something about her that...
she's one of them sex kitten-
type girls, and I like it.
>> I will be... I'll be totally
honest with you.
If you saw my season, you can
know that when I say I'm going
to stick to something and do
it...
>> Yeah.
I... you know what?
It's so funny that you're here,
because you're, like, one of my
favorite players.
I don't know, I think that's
really cool.
I'd say I have pretty keen
powers of observation, and from
what I can tell, Amanda and Ozzy
have this rapport with one
another already.
>> And you're, like, the loyal
one, you know?
Like, I think that's so awesome.
>> And ever since we got here,
Parvati hasn't been able to take
her hands or eyes off of James.
She is definitely going to have
him wrapped around her finger.
So I think there definitely
could be romance bubbling
between both Parvati and James
and Amanda and Ozzy.
And so that makes all four of
them very dangerous.
>> Good night, John Boy.
>> Good night, favorites.
>> Palm fronds.
Do we need anything more?
>> Yeah, let's put the fronds on
the ground, too.
>> That's a good idea.
>> Is anybody over here?
>> Here comes another one.
>> Tonight is night number one,
and we kind of took a little too
long to find a location to build
our shelter, and it didn't come
along as planned.
>> Holy crap.
>> Tonight's the first night
here, and the downpour, it came
and it was hard, and it didn't
stop.
( thunder )
I hope by morning I feel a whole
lot better, because right now
this sucks.
( crying )
>> I know you are.
>> I think that...
>> This would be awesome.
>> We would be a really good
group.
>> Yeah, why don't we stick
together starting now?
>> Starting now?
>> We're not supposed to scheme
until tomorrow.
>> Come on, everyone else is
scheming.
>> I love it.
>> Hands in, I'll do it.
>> I'll do it.
>> All right.
>> I love you guys.
>> I love you guys!
This is it.
>> Okay, done.
>> Ami, Yau-Man, Jonathan, and
myself, the four of us are a
tight alliance.
But the problem is, it seems
like there's another foursome
out here, and that is Amanda and
Ozzy and Parvati and James.
We're very concerned about that
foursome.
And we were worried they would
try to pull in Fairplay and
Cirie.
We need a fifth.
>> I say Fairplay.
Yeah.
>> Wait a minute.
>> Yeah.
We have turn on him before he
turns on us.
>> I don't trust him.
>> Okay.
So who all do we have?
>> Us three.
>> Yeah.
>> We can get James and Amanda
for sure.
One, two, three, four, five.
>> We are a little wary of Eliza
just hearing about the way she
played the game in Vanuatu.
She's shifty, crafty.
Some of us just feel like we
can't trust her.
>> I'm easy, man.
Trust me.
>> I'm a little nervous because
Fairplay's got his villain
persona to live up to, so maybe
he will just betray everyone he
can.
I don't know.
But at this point, we need
Fairplay to make a strong
alliance.
>> Let's go swimming.
>> Good.
>> So we were productive.
>> Yes.
>> Jonny Fairplay is sitting
back right now being friends
with everybody.
I'm a very likable person.
I'm a very nice person.
I just have the ability to lie
very easily, which comes in
handy here.
>> Hey, hey.
James, Amanda, Ozzy, and Parvati
are a done deal alliance of
four.
>> Absolutely.
>> So we need to make a counter.
>> They want what?
>> Me.
>> Ozzy or Parvati.
It doesn't matter to me.
>> I say Parvati first.
>> I say Parvati, too.
>> With Parvati still in, she
can manipulate crap in the way
Ozzy could never...
I think we should take Parvati
out first.
I think Parvati is a much bigger
threat as a social player than
Ozzy is.
>> Fairplay pretends he's with
them, and I act like everything
is perfect.
>> I'll play the game.
>> Fairplay's a gem to have on
your alliance.
He needs us much more than we
need him.
You keep him around for as long
as possible.
Hell, I'd take Fairplay to the
end if I could.
Do they think you are with them?
>> Yeah.
>> I think it's insane that
there's nine other of your
favorite Survivors of all time,
and they all believe what I say.
Have you not watched the show
before?
>> Yau-Man!
Do you think you have enough sun
you can start with your glasses?
>> I can feel burning.
I'm trying to focus the sun onto
this quote, unquote dry coconut
husk with a drop of water on my
glasses to act as a magnifying
glass.
It's a very nice magnifying
The sun is almost vertical
enough that this should work.
It worked in Fiji.
>> It's so warm.
>> I know.
It's unbelievably warm.
>> It's like pee water.
>> Wow, it's burning.
>> Yeah, Yau-Man.
Yeah.
Yo, we need wood.
>> Oh, my god!
>> Oh, my god, they started it.
>> Woo!
>> Yea.
>> Good job, dude.
>> Yau-Man got our fire started
miraculously.
We're all very excited.
We have fire.
We've been eating.
We've been drinking.
We're all well rested, well
hydrated, and we're ready to
kick some butt.
>> I hope we have something.
>> We have tree mail.
>> Woo!
Yes!
Hey, guys, we've got tree mail!
>> Hey, we got tree mail.
>> Tree mail!
>> It's a puzzle.
>> Yeah, I love puzzles.
>> It says, "16 seasons later,
you all should know the deal.
Outwit, outplay, outlast.
Don't waste time reinventing the
wheel."
>> I think everybody is, you
know, biting at the bit just to
get in the game.
And I think the favorites are
chuckling at us right now,
saying that we're going to be a
piece of cake, that they're
going to walk all over us.
>> "Don't reinvent the wheel"
means don't be stupid.
>> It means don't be too smart.
Don't outthink yourself.
>> They're not looking at us as
competitors.
But that's good.
Even better-- underdog, we'll
take that role.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
Deja vu.
( laughter )
So here we are, our first
challenge.
Eliza, you guys have played this
game before.
Did you see the advantage you
had now in getting a shelter up
quickly?
>> Jeff, have no idea how much
of an advantage we have.
Not only do we have a shelter,
but we have fire, we have food,
we all have full bellies.
We are so excited and so pumped
for this challenge, ready to
kick some butt.
>> We're doing three courses for
every meal.
It's ridiculous.
I'm getting fat.
I have gained weight since I've
been here.
>> JEFF: Joel, you buying all
this?
>> No.
>> ( laughter )
>> You guys are dumber than you
look.
>> But, hey, you know, if it is,
good for them.
They can get fat and happy, and
we can win the challenges.
>> JEFF: Here's how it works--
on my go, you must race to
assemble four wheels and place
them on your cart.
You must then push your cart
through a series of obstacles.
When you reach the sand pit you
must dig up a bundle of planks.
You'll use the planks to fill in
gaps in the bridge.
Push your cart over your bridge
to the finished platform, where
you must then take the wheels
off of your cart and use them to
complete a turnstile.
Finally, you'll use the
turnstile to raise a fire wok,
lighting the top of the
platform.
First tribe to finish wins.
You know to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes!
>> JEFF: Immunity.
When you have immunity in your
possession, you cannot be voted
out.
In addition, the winning tribe
gets fire in the form of flint.
All right, give you a minute to
strategize.
>> Come on, guys, right here.
Right here.
>> Kick this some fan ass right
now.
>> JEFF: Here we go, the first
challenge of fans versus
favorites.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> JEFF: Have to assemble the
four wheels, then put them on
your cart.
>> Come on, come on, come on,
come on!
>> I got it, I got it, I got it.
>> Come on, guys, quickly,
quickly!
>> Take your time.
>> Stand back and look at it.
>> Guys, guys, guys!
>> We got it.
>> JEFF: Fans have their four
wheels.
>> Amanda, behind you!
Behind you, Amanda!
>> JEFF: Favorites having no
luck putting their four wheels
together.
>> Come on, guys.
It's okay.
Take your time!
Calm down.
Look at it!
>> All right, take your time.
>> Let's go!
>> Come on, guys!
We've got this.
>> JEFF: The fans are off.
Favorites still working.
>> Relax.
>> JEFF: Falling behind.
>> Look at that one.
>> JEFF: Fans extending their
lead.
>> Come on!
>> We can still do it, you guys.
We can still do it.
>> JEFF: Fans working through
the obstacle.
Jason, Joel, Mikey B tearing it
up.
>> One, two, three!
>> Here comes the cart, rolling
over their tribe.
>> Not yet, not yet.
>> Go!
Yes!
>> JEFF: Fans are through the
obstacle.
>> Go, go, go!
>> JEFF: Favorites have their
cart.
They are back in this!
>> Whoa!
>> JEFF: An absolute wipeout for
the favorites.
>> Are you okay?
>> JEFF: This challenge is
falling apart for the favorites.
>> Oh!
>> JEFF: Fans still with a good-
sized lead.
They are now digging up the
planks.
Favorites trying to get back on
course after a big wipeout.
>> These wheels aren't turning.
>> Come on, guys.
We still can do this.
>> Go to your right.
Go to your right a little bit.
>> Watch out for the tree!
>> Favorites starting to make up
some ground.
>> JEFF: Fans have their planks
out on the sand, got to untie
them.
Here come the favorites.
They're back in it!
Dig!
Dig, dig, dig!
>> JEFF: Erik giving a little
greeting to the favorites,
trying to distract him while his
tribe continues to work with the
planks.
Fans are very much in control,
taking their time.
>> Another one!
>> JEFF: Building their bridge.
>> James, you got this!
Go, guys, go!
Good job, guys.
>> JEFF: Fans first over the
bridge!
Favorites have their planks!
They're back in this!
>> Plank.
>> Plank, plank, plank.
>> Come on, let's go!
Let's go!
>> Come on!
>> JEFF: Favorites are now
building their bridge.
Fans already have their bridge
completed.
>> Get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
>> JEFF: And a wipeout into the
tree.
Favorites now taking on their
bridge.
They're still in it.
>> Line it up, line it up!
>> Go, go, go!
>> Hurry!
>> Push!
>> JEFF: Favorites still trying
to make their way over the
bridge.
>> One person at each place.
>> JEFF: Fans quickly get the
wheels off their cart, and
they're working on the
turnstile.
>> Go!
>> Go, go, go!
>> JEFF: Favorites are now down
the bridge and making their way!
Fans working together very well.
>> Turn them around.
>> Pull the cart up!
>> JEFF: Got to finish the
turnstile using the pieces of
the wheels.
Fans getting closer.
Favorites now quickly trying to
work on their puzzle.
>> Go!
>> JEFF: Fans have their
turnstile complete.
They've got to raise the wok to
the top of the platform.
Favorites trying to get into
this.
The first immunity challenge...
is won by the fans!
>> JEFF: Fans, congratulations.
Immunity.
Nobody going home tonight.
And fire in the form of flint.
( cheering )
>> JEFF: Favorites, you know
this drill.
Date with me tonight at tribal
council, where one of the
favorites will have the
distinction as being the first
person voted out of Fans versus
Favorites.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you tonight at tribal.
>> That sucked.
>> We tried hard, lost.
no shame in losing.
These fans are so excited, so
enthusiastic.
I mean, they're playing
Survivor.
It's their dream.
And they just had more heart out
there.
>> The loss, it's going to
humble us and make us ready to
kick ass in the next one.
>> I may not swim as well as
Ozzy, but I think I did pretty
good today.
>> Yeah, you did.
>> We're going to tribal council
and gosh, I do not have a plan
at all.
I have no idea what I'm going to
do right now.
I don't really trust any of
these people.
I don't care.
I'll get rid of anybody, as long
as it's not me.
>> What am I good at?
>> Yeah.
>> I think I'm good for morale,
entertainment value.
That's about it.
( laughter )
Right now, I could go either way
and totally change the game in
two different directions.
Two groups I'm playing are the
four of Yau-Man, Eliza,
Jonathan, Ami.
>> Yep.
>> And then you have the
alliance of Ozzy, James, Parvati
and Amanda.
They're after Eliza.
So we'll see.
People don't understand, like,
what crazy thing are you going
to do?
I'm like, how about the crazy
thing is, I don't do anything?
I just want to see my
girlfriend.
That's it.
>> You must miss her really bad?
>> Yeah.
She's seven months pregnant, and
like, you know, I don't know
anything.
I think about my girlfriend and
my upcoming little girl every
single second out here, and I
want to win this game for them.
I can't stop thinking that maybe
there's something wrong with my
little girl.
( crying )
I'll tell you what, a million
dollars is great.
But having a healthy little
girl, that's the biggest prize I
could win right now.
>> Shut up.
You'll ruin our whole plan.
Maybe you should, though.
>> What's that?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know.
I mean, it might be just too
crazy, but I came up with this
little plan to distract
Jonathan, Eliza, Yau-Man, and
Ami into voting for Fairplay,
and we're all voting for Eliza,
just because I don't want Eliza
turning around and trying to,
you know, snake me.
>> I mean, having a kid is a
pretty powerful thing.
>> Yeah.
>> You know?
>> I'm just emotionally not
here.
So, I mean, I'm sorry.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm just... I can't... you
know.
>> Is there any way that I can
talk you into staying in?
>> No.
I'm sorry.
>> Yeah, it sucks.
Fairplay is a loose cannon.
Fairplay said to me that he
wanted to go home.
He just puts you on your serious
stance guard, because you don't
know ever what he means.
>> He does not want to be here.
>> He doesn't want to stay?
>> He does not want to stay.
>> Or is he just saying that so
we all vote for him and he is
with them?
We've just got to be careful
because he could pull a fast
one.
I've just got to make sure he
doesn't do anything crazy.
I'm a little worried that
Fairplay is going to come
together with James, Ozzy,
Amanda, and Parvati.
All I know is tonight, tribal
council is going to be crazy,
because if I know Jonny
Fairplay, he is going to stir
things up.
>> I'm ready.
Let's battle!
Tribal council!
>> JEFF: Behind each of you is a
torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
approach the flame.
This is part of the ritual of
tribal council, because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have that fire,
you're in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
Jonny Fairplay, you guys have
all played this game.
Everybody here should come in
fairly well versed in terms of
what is required.
How did it go when you got to
camp?
>> Cake.
I mean, food is a lot easier
here.
We've made an amazing shelter.
So I think our only problem was,
I'm guessing, over-confidence.
>> JEFF: Eliza, let's talk about
past reputations.
How big a factor are reputations
coming into this game?
>> It's definitely a factor.
I mean, whether or not somebody
says, "Oh, I'm just going to get
to know you for you," it doesn't
matter.
That's going to be in the back
of their head.
They're going to remember the
things you do, the moves you
made, how you interacted with
people, and that's going to
probably play a factor in the
way people vote.
>> JEFF: Jonny Fairplay,
probably nobody in this game has
a bigger reputation than you.
>> I agree.
>> JEFF: Can that be an
advantage?
>> Honestly, I think everyone
here was kind of surprised with
the real Jonny Fairplay, I
guess, and I can easily say I
feel that all of them trust me.
But at the same time, like, my
head's kind of screwed up right
now.
I have a little baby on the way.
And honestly, all I think about,
"Is my little baby Piper okay?"
You know, like, that's all that
goes through my head.
I'm like, you know, "Am I being
a crappy dad by being here?"
>> JEFF: But you're not a father
yet.
>> Yeah, I'm this close.
I mean, I had no idea that I was
going to think like this once I
got here.
I mean, I don't have a kid.
I'm about to have one, and guess
what?
It changes you.
It changes your head.
It makes you crazy.
>> JEFF: So you want to go home,
or you had a bad afternoon and
now you're trying to recover?
>> You know, last time I learned
to be Jonny Fairplay and be an
ass ( no audio ).
This time, you know, what?
If I learn to be a good dad, so
be it.
So I mean, I'm just... you know,
my head is screwy right now.
>> JEFF: Why are you smiling,
Yau-Man?
>> Well, because my first
thought is, you know, what's the
scheme?
It's a very strange thing to say
to us suddenly just out of the
blue.
>> JEFF: Ozzy, is this just
simply a case of Fairplay can't
hack it, it's much harder than
he remembered, and he wanted to
go home?
>> Jeff, I'll honestly tell you,
no, I don't think so.
>> You can say what you want,
Jeff.
I don't need to put on a little
show for you.
I mean, honestly, like, I'm
screwy right now.
You know, emotions are going
crazy in my head, and that's it.
And it wasn't supposed to be
this difficult.
>> JEFF: Jonathan, Fairplay has
a reputation of pulling scams
and lying.
Just to be clear, what is he
doing?
>> I think he's asking us to
vote for him.
I think, you know, somebody has
to go home.
Somebody wants to go home.
And he's going to go home.
>> JEFF: So it's a quit?
>> This is not a quit.
>> JEFF: Forgive my skepticism,
but last time you cried over a
dead grandma who conveniently
was at home watching on TV.
>> I understand.
>> JEFF: Yes or no answer-- is
this a quit?
Eliza?
>> No.
>> JEFF: This is not a quit?
>> There is still a possibility
in my mind that Fairplay is not
going home tonight.
I mean, I don't think there's
one person who didn't bring
their stuff with them.
So we're still voting.
>> JEFF: Oh, we are voting.
All right, Yau-Man, you have the
immunity idol.
It is only good tonight.
You can use it for yourself...
>> No, I'm keeping it.
>> JEFF: All right, you cannot
vote for Yau-Man.
Everybody else, including Mr.
Fairplay, is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Ami, you're up.
>> Jonny I've got to vote for
you.
You've asked me to.
I wish you the best of luck,
and...
>> Jonny, if you need any advice
how to raise a baby to be a
happy and well-adjusted child, I
will be very happy to give you
some advice.
Thank you.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
First vote, Fairplay.
Fairplay.
Two votes Fairplay.
That's three votes Fairplay.
Fairplay.
Four votes Fairplay.
That's five votes Fairplay.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Fans Versus
Favorites, Jonny Fairplay.
That's six, that's enough.
You need to grab your torch.
Jonny Fairplay, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Can I get a hug?
You be nice to those guys!
Bye, guys.
>> JEFF: Well, I never would
have predicted that.
Good news is because you've been
to tribal council, you get fire
in the form of flint.
Yau-Man, you can leave that idol
behind.
It's of no use anymore.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor:
>> Why is everyone talking all
the time and not working?
>> JEFF: The fans are in
turmoil.
>> Emotionally, it's not good
for me to be here.
>> JEFF: The rules have changed
at Exile Island.
Two people, one idol.
>> Wow.
>> JEFF: And two castaways have
a night to remember.
>> Go get a hotel room.
>> I definitely feel I did the
right thing.
I had every single person here
eating out of the palm of my
hand, and to go out on my own
terms, I'm very happy with that.
No regrets at all.
Last time I was the biggest bad
guy ever, and this time I'm a
responsible adult that people
liked, some even loved.
What's going on in the world?