>> JEFF: Previously on Survivor,
ten of Survivor's biggest fans
were pitted against ten
favorites from seasons past.
Both tribes immediately competed
for a shot at individual
immunity.
Yau-Man narrowly won the idol
for the favorites, and he helped
Kathy find the idol for the
fans.
>> Pick up that!
>> JEFF: The fans struggled on
their beach and failed to build
a solid shelter.
>> JEFF: Go!
At the first immunity challenge,
the favorites relied on
experience, but experience
wasn't enough.
The first immunity challenge is
won by the fans!
Facing tribal council, the
favorites were split into two
alliances.
>> Ami, Yau-Man, Jonathan and
myself, the four of us are a
tight alliance, but there's
another foursome out here--
Amanda and Ozzy and Parvati and
James.
>> JEFF: And both groups wanted
to recruit the same player.
>> We need a fifth.
>> I say Fairplay.
>> We need Fairplay to make a
strong alliance.
>> JEFF: But Fairplay made a
surprising revelation to his
tribe.
>> JEFF: Not everyone was
convinced he was telling the
truth.
>> If I know Jonny Fairplay, he
is going to pull something out
of his hat that none of us are
going to be expecting, and he is
going to stir things up.
>> JEFF: But in the end, the
entire tribe wrote down his
name, and severed ties with one
of the most infamous players to
play the game.
Jonny Fairplay, the tribe has
spoken.
19 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I can't believe you just
caught that fish with your bare
hands.
>> I know.
How awesome is that?
>> Yes, guys, we lost Fairplay,
but we did gain a fish.
Maybe that's a good omen.
>> How awesome is it we came
back and now we're eating fish?
>> I know.
A late-night snack.
>> Well, we had tribal council
tonight, and Jonny Fairplay had
asked us to vote him off.
And I kept thinking something
was going to change, something
was gone going to happen,
something terrible-- that I was
going to be the one going home
first.
But we took him seriously and we
honored his request.
>> There was just too much going
on for him, which is weird,
because he seemed to be holding
it together.
I was not pleased when Jonny
pulled this, because it screwed
up my plans.
But you know what?
Everybody knows that if we can
continue to do what we're doing,
we should be able to win.
>> I'll tell you what, it is
delicious.
I mean, I figure that if
everyone had been out here for
30, 33, 39 days, something like
that, times nine, that's
basically a year's worth of
experience.
We're just feeling confident
that we can go in there and beat
these guys at almost any
challenge.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> But there's still a lot of
stuff we need to do.
>> We need water.
>> All this needs to be cleared
because it smells like...
>> It's day four, and we're in a
bad place right now.
We need to fix our shelter.
We haven't had any water.
Everyone is tired.
Everyone is hungry.
But at the challenge yesterday,
we beat the favorites, won
immunity, and along with
immunity, we also won flint, and
flint is fire.
So we're golden.
As soon as I light this, it's
going to ignite immediately.
>> Like, boom!
>> Woo!
>> Keep it going, keep it going.
>> Keep blowing.
Blow more.
>> How much of this do we have
left?
>> We've got to make fire!
I don't care how much we have!
>> At some point, we've got to
give up and say...
>> What are they doing now with
the fire?
Do we know?
Let's go find out.
>> The boys are still back there
trying to start a fire.
They're all chopping away, but
we've got nothing!
Number one priority for me is
shelter, because pretty much
every night it rains.
So let's go and let's do it.
What is the problem?
I don't understand.
>> Why is everybody talking all
the time and not working?
>> Oh, this will be the worst
night in the history of our
lives.
>> We've got no shelter.
Nothing.
>> Yeah.
>> Then let's all... can we all
get in on it and start humping
it?
>> No, they're not going to help
build a shelter.
They're going to go dig for
wood.
>> I just spent a half hour
trying to do fire!
All you do is run your mouth.
>> And we have not had to go to
tribal council yet, and there's
drama!
>> We can clean out that cave,
shush it out with some palm
fronds, lay some down, and we
can sleep clean and dry tonight.
See, they're already cleaning it
out.
Oh, those rat bastards.
>> Yeah.
>> This is exactly what we were
getting ready to do.
>> We were going to come and
clean it out and put some palm
fronds down, and that was going
to be home tonight.
>> No, this is my habitat
tonight.
>> Tracy, Kathy, and Chet, I
don't think they accomplished a
single productive thing all day
long.
And I just don't even want to be
around them, so I told them
straight up, I was like, "I
don't want you sleeping in the
cave."
>> I'm not going to fight with
these kids, you know?
I mean, they hate us.
Come on.
>> Tracy, Chet, and myself have
pretty much been shunned by the
other people.
And you can't fight seven
against three.
It just makes you relive things
in your life-- high school,
whatever-- when you didn't fit
in and you were kind of outcast.
It just kind of brings it all
back.
>> Yeah, let's do that.
Let's grab it.
>> Oh, they took it.
>> They just took it.
>> Okay, okay.
>> Tell me we're not divided.
>> We were quite disorganized in
the last challenge, so we're
going to try to do a little
better today.
And we're hoping that the fans
have slept poorly and are still
way behind us on the camp curve,
because we're doing great, I
mean, honestly.
>> And we thought this one was
big.
>> Yeah.
>> Right?
I'm starting to become... I'm
starting to become really
attracted to Amanda.
She is so cute.
I mean, she's beautiful, and
it's like... oh, we've just got
to stay apart as long as
possible, because if it becomes
obvious to the group, then I'm
going to have a giant target on
my back.
I wonder if we'll get some
sharks.
>> I hope so.
>> Watch out.
>> That's the same color I
found.
I started off working out a
flirting angle with James, and
it was just so easy because he's
just so cute, you know?
>> What do you think, Amanda, is
it love?
>> I don't know.
I definitely think that James
and Parvati have something going
on.
And, you know, I've always
thought Ozzy was really, really
cute, and so it's kind of like a
couple-y alliance, yeah.
But we just have to be careful,
because I don't want it to screw
up my game.
>> I'm going to finally get some
sleep.
>> Well, this worked out
beautiful.
>> Imagine that.
>> And it's solid.
>> Kathy, Chet, and myself, we
made a new shelter for the three
of us, and we're going to make
it our home.
>> I like how they did that on
part of their wall.
>> Definitely.
That's a crazy covering.
That's awesome.
>> I think if we build it here
and you guys have already have
yours, and we have a fire in the
middle, then we can all just sit
down and just bury the hatchet.
>> Clean that out and use the
back of the tree.
>> No, I would like you to, yes,
please.
>> The other seven, they came
over and asked me to help them
build their new shelter, so I
think that I've earned a little
bit of respect from them.
But right now, all I care about
is getting a fire, because if I
don't get some water in me, I'm
going to die.
>> We are going to get it right
now.
>> We are.
>> Blow, blow.
Keep blowing.
>> Get some little sticks in
there.
>> There we go!
>> Yes!
>> We made fire!
Feels so good!
>> Finally, we got fire.
Now we can boil water.
We actually found some clams,
so we're going to get some food
in our bellies, and it's
definitely a really good
feeling.
>> Food, finally!
>> Oh, my god!
Oh!
>> That is so good!
>> Oh, boy!
>> The whole dynamic of the
tribe just completely turned
around.
>> Everybody seems to kind of
put their issues behind them,
and we're much more unified as a
tribe.
And what's that right in the
middle?
>> A ticket stub.
I go to a lot of ball games and
a lot of concerts.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my God, I love it.
>> I'm definitely flirting with
Mary, absolutely.
She's a cute girl and I'm having
fun with her on the island.
She's a friendly, funny girl to
get along with.
I want to get Mary to trust me,
and if I can use my flirtatious
ability to get her in my back
pocket, then I'm going to use
it.
Come here.
>> Oh, god.
>> Protein!
Protein!
>> Mikey, I think, really likes
how Mary looks, and has
maneuvered himself pretty close
to her.
That's right out of, you know,
Player School 101, I think.
So obviously, I'm going to keep
my eyes on them.
But my priority right now is to
keep my tribe strong, so I think
the three outsiders, Tracy,
Chet, and Kathy, they'll be out
of here as soon as possible.
>> I was awake quite a bit last
night, and I heard the sounds
of...
...jungle love, I guess.
I think we'll be receiving birth
announcements from Amanda on
her little Ozzlets she's about
to have.
And Parvati and James will be at
the wedding as soon as this is
over.
So yeah, it's a little more than
just alliances there with those
guys, so that's what makes it
scary.
>> It's silly, you know?
Go get a hotel room.
I mean, you've got to take one
step back and say, "There might
be somebody awake."
We are sleeping together in a
cave, you know.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> The two couples separate
don't really bother me, but the
four of them together poses a
problem.
I don't know just yet how I'm
going to dismantle that
foursome.
But I'm going to try.
>> Okay.
We have myself, Eliza, Ami, Yau-
Man-- there's a core four-- and
we needed one more for the lock,
and that was Cirie, who just
told me that she will work with
me down the line if we decide to
go that far together.
>> JEFF: Come on in, guys!
Fans getting your first look at
the new favorites tribe.
Jonny Fairplay voted out at the
first tribal council.
>> Good job, guys!
Good job.
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yep.
>> JEFF: First things, first.
Mary, I will take it back.
>> I don't want to give it.
>> JEFF: Immunity is back up for
grabs.
For today's challenge, each
tribe will select five swimmers,
three puzzle makers, and one
keymaster.
On my go, the first person will
race out to a platform, climb to
the top, then smash a tile,
releasing a key, dive down,
retrieve the key, get back to
shore.
Collect all five keys.
Then the keymaster will open a
chest containing puzzle pieces.
The puzzle makers will then take
these pieces and assemble a
puzzle map of Micronesia.
The first tribe to finish wins.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> JEFF: Winning tribe wins
immunity and is safe from tribal
council.
And you're playing for a
reward-- fishing gear...
>> All right!
>> JEFF: ...as well as a bamboo
fishing boat that will be
waiting for you back at camp.
>> Oh, nice!
>> JEFF: There's more.
The winning tribe will also
select one person from the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island.
The bad news about Exile
Island-- you're separated from
your tribe.
The good news-- hidden somewhere
on Exile Island is a hidden
immunity idol.
Find that idol, you have power
in this game.
There is one other twist in this
challenge, which I will tell you
after this challenge is over.
>> Oh, god!
>> JEFF: It's a lot, plus
immunity.
Worth playing for?
>> Absolutely.
>> JEFF: Fans, you have one
extra member.
Sitting somebody out.
Who's it going to be?
>> Okay, I guess I am.
>> JEFF: Kathy will have a spot
on the bench.
I'll give you guys a minute to
strategize, we'll get started.
Here we go, for immunity and
reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Ozzy and Jason across the lily
pads.
Ozzy makes it, Jason doesn't.
>> Come on, Jason!
You got it, baby, nice.
>> JEFF: Ozzy making fast work
of that swim, already at the
platform.
Ozzy not even hesitating.
Smashes the tile.
He's in the water with the key.
Jason obliterates his tile.
Ozzy has the key, and he's
heading back.
>> Yeah, Ozzy!
>> JEFF: Jason has the key for
the fans.
>> Go, Jason!
>> JEFF: Ozzy back.
Ami now heading back out for the
favorites.
Jason back with the first key
for the fans.
Alexis heading out over the lily
pads.
Ami is on the platform.
Alexis trying to close the gap.
>> Alexis, go, go, go!
>> Go, Alexis!
>> JEFF: Ami heading back to
shore with the second key for
the favorites.
Alexis has her key.
>> Good job, Lexy, hustle it in!
Great job.
>> JEFF: Ami back with the
second key.
Go, Amanda.
Amanda heading out on the
course.
Alexis back with the second key
for the fans.
Chet now on the course, takes a
big fall.
We are tied, two keys each.
Amanda at the platform, breaks a
tile, and the key is in the
water.
Amanda has the third key for the
favorites.
>> Watch it fall, Chet.
Watch it fall.
>> JEFF: Chet obliterates his
tile.
Chet cannot find the key.
Amanda back with that third key
for the favorites.
Parvati on the course.
>> Chet!
It's in front of you to the
right!
>> It's right there, Chet.
You've got to go down, bro.
>> JEFF: Parvati at the
platform.
Parvati breaks her tile.
Key is in the water.
>> Chet, get out of the water!
Let's go!
Get out!
>> Come back, come back, come
back!
>> JEFF: Parvati has the fourth
key for the favorites.
She's heading back.
>> Yeah, Parv!
>> Get out of the water!
Come on, man!
>> Hustle.
You've got to do this.
>> JEFF: Parvati is back.
Penner heading out, the last
person to go for the favorites.
Mikey B Heading out for the
fans.
>> Let's go, Mikey!
We've still got this.
>> JEFF: Jonathan increasing the
lead for the favorites.
Jonathan can't find his key.
Mikey B. trying to make up some
time.
>> Jonathan, other way, other
way!
Right in front of you.
>> JEFF: Mikey B. back with that
third key.
>> Let's go, Erik!
Let's go, Erik.
>> JEFF: Erik out on the course.
Penner has the fifth and final
key for the favorites.
>> Yeah, Jonathan!
>> JEFF: Erik not giving up.
>> Let's go, Erik.
You got it!
>> JEFF: Erik knocks his tile.
Penner back with the fifth and
final key for the favorites!
James starting to work on the
chest.
Erik has his key.
Chet's is still in the water.
Five keys, five locks.
James has two locks undone.
One key left in the water for
the fans.
You're still in this.
Jason back out to retrieve
Chet's key.
James now has four locks open.
James has all five open.
Favorites start working on the
puzzle.
>> We've got to get the pieces
out.
So we can see them.
>> JEFF: Eliza, Cirie, Yau-Man,
trying to figure out the key to
this puzzle.
It is a map of Micronesia.
Jason heading back with the
fifth key for the fans.
>> This one goes here.
>> JEFF: Favorites think they're
getting close.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Here it goes.
>> That's it, that's it!
>> JEFF: Favorites win immunity!
And reward.
>> We did it!
>> Woo!
Yes!
Oh, my god!
>> JEFF: Favorites,
congratulations.
>> Thanks!
>> JEFF: Nobody going home from
the favorites.
In addition, all this fishing
gear and a bamboo fishing boat
waiting for you back at camp.
One more thing to deal with--
you must now choose somebody
from the tribe of fans to send
to Exile Island, and they will
return to camp in the morning in
time for tribal council.
>> Yeah.
Kathy, yeah, all right.
>> JEFF: Who's it going to be?
Who are you sending to exile?
>> The one...
>> Kathy.
>> ...with the hat.
>> JEFF: Kathy, before I send
you on your way, we'll get to
the twist I told about.
Tribe of favorites, you must now
choose somebody from your own
tribe to join Kathy on Exile
Island.
Two people, one idol.
>> Wow.
>> JEFF: You will both spend the
night together on Exile.
You will both get the first clue
to the location of the hidden
immunity idol.
>> Cirie is going to go.
>> JEFF: All right, Kathy and
Cirie, grab your stuff.
The boat's waiting.
>> Bye, Kathy.
>> Bye.
>> JEFF: Fans, nothing else for
you except a date with me
tomorrow night at tribal
council, where one of you will
be going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Exile Island, that I never
got to go to.
>> That's right, you never got
to go.
>> Well, I'm here now.
>> I think staying here on Exile
Island with Cirie is actually a
good thing.
Watching her from her season,
she really grew a lot.
And she's so sweet.
She's so motherly.
She's right there.
>> Let's go.
We've got to move quick, because
we're not going to have a lot of
time before it gets dark.
>> You've got to climb.
The part about "go to the
start," they're not talking the
start of our own island, are
they?
>> It can't be-- aahh!
I'm thinking, let's go back.
Right now, my team is nine
people.
There's Parvati and those guys,
and Jonathan and those guys, and
then I'm smack dab in the
middle.
So all I was thinking is I'm
going to Exile Island, god,
please help me find the hidden
immunity idol.
What?
>> Why another clue?
>> "Clue number two, continue
your quest by crossing the
ocean.
You've done it before, now
repeat the motion."
>> Right over there.
Damn, again?
>> Into the forest.
>> We just came from over here
and now we've got to go over
here.
>> And we have to do it quick,
because we're burning daylight,
girl.
We're going to go there.
>> Looking for the idol was
absolute torture.
The second clue, it tells you
that the third clue is across
another part of the ocean.
>> I got it!
Come here!
Hurry up!
It better not be another clue.
I swear to god...
>> I'm just seeing those two
things, looks like legs, those
two sticks.
>> Oh, right here?
>> I'm looking in the middle of
the ocean to see two things pop
up.
>> So then, we find the third
clue, back across the ocean.
>> Because it says, "You'll find
more to this lore."
>> I've never worked so hard,
walked so far in my life.
>> Get to the fourth clue, back
across the ocean.
Oh, my god!
By the time we found the fourth
clue, I was so tired and so
frustrated.
And we searched and searched and
searched and searched.
>> I know, it's almost like,
okay, you can come out now,
idol.
We give up.
>> We can't get this close and
then not find it.
>> I know.
>> We need to get some coconuts
and get the shelter ready, get
ready to get some water.
>> I think we need a round of
applause for everyone today.
Because no matter what, we come
together as a team, we win and
lose as a team.
>> I give it to all of you that
swam.
>> It was a lot tougher.
>> We lost our challenge today,
so this is our first time going
to tribal council.
I mean, that's a big deal, and
we're all very frustrated.
I don't care about losing the
immunity.
I care about the fishing stuff,
because that box is a box of
gold, you know?
There was everything there.
It's most likely going to be one
of the three older members of
the tribe going home, probably
Chet, because he did very, very
poorly in the challenge.
I mean, he was floundering
around.
If Chet's strength is what he
showed today, then come on.
There's no discussion as far as
I'm concerned.
All of us know who we want to go
home.
That would be Chet.
But there's all these variables
that come into play which makes
it difficult.
Okay, and then the girls vote
Tracy.
And then they're going to have
their three votes versus you,
okay?
So that's four to three, and
Chet goes home.
I'm suggesting splitting our
votes, four to Chet and three to
Tracy, just in case Kathy found
the hidden immunity on Exile
Island.
If she had it, they can give it
to Chet or Tracy, and then if we
vote them, it bounces back to
us, and we're screwed.
If Kathy gives the immunity idol
to Chet, us guys, us four, vote
for Tracy, and the girls, the
three, vote for Kathy.
>> Wait, wait, wait.
That's in the case of what?
>> If she gives it to Chet.
>> Yeah.
>> Now, the only way we can get
screwed is if Kathy gave Tracy
the immunity, and then it goes
to a tiebreaker.
>> We have to stick to it.
That's what I'm saying.
Let's get the final plan right
now and we don't have to talk
about it again.
>> Mike is throwing out all of
his different scenarios on what
if Kathy found the immunity idol
on Exile Island?
She already has an immunity idol
from a previous challenge, on
and on and on and on, so much so
that it confuses me.
My initial thought was, "Chet,
you're out of here.
You're done."
But Mikey thinks he's got it all
figured out, and I don't like
that.
He's teamed up with Mary, and
now he thinks he has pretty much
the entire tribe voting the way
he wants us to vote, and doing
whatever he wants.
But if I have anything to say
about that at tribal council
tomorrow night, it will be
abundantly clear that that's not
the case.
>> Yesterday we lost the
immunity challenge, so tonight
we're all going to tribal
council.
And Mikey seems to think that
he's running the show over here.
And I just want to put a stop to
it.
Mikey and Mary are very close,
and I believe that if we have
one person who believes that
they are leading this tribe in a
certain direction, their
strongest alliance, in my mind,
would be the alliance to break.
If you take away Mary, that's
his closest ally.
>> Joel suggested we, along with
Alexis, work together to get rid
of Mary.
And it could be a good idea.
Because Mikey is a really smart
guy, and he knows what he's
doing here.
That's pretty diabolical, but I
mean, come on.
>> It's what the game is, bro.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's Kathy.
>> Want to try to get rid of
Mary and break up the Mike and
Mary?
>> Oh, my god, it's just a
little tiny piece of beach, and
that's it.
>> How was it out there?
>> Cirie is one of the nicest
people I ever met in my entire
life.
No, I curled up in a fetal
position.
So what's going on around here
with you guys as far as tribal
council?
>> That's all I'm telling you.
Just do it.
Just write it down.
>> I was super worried that they
were all going to pick Chet, and
when I come back from Exile
Island, boy, right away, Joel
steps up to me and goes, "It's
Mary."
I'm like, "Where did Mary come
from?"
>> Don't spill the beans before
we vote.
>> You have to tell me what I
can say and what I can't say.
>> It's like I tell my pageant
girls-- answer the question and
shut up.
Don't ramble.
Get off the stage.
>> Over the last two days, it
was Kathy, Chet, and myself
against the other seven.
And now we finally see a window
of opportunity, but I just don't
know if I can trust Joel.
Joel wants this million dollars,
I think, probably more than
anybody here.
And I feel that he's going to
stop at nothing to get it.
>> We've got a plan.
Don't talk to anybody else about
it.
>> Joel's pulled Natalie aside,
talked to her a little bit, so
we don't know really what
they're talking about, but we
just need to be really honest
with ourselves, and where the
weaknesses lie.
>> All of us guys vote Chet, and
if she gives the immunity to
Chet, we all vote Tracy.
Girls all voting Tracy.
>> There might be a little
confusion as far as our vote
tonight, but I really feel at
this point I can trust Alexis, I
can trust Mike, I can trust
Natalie.
So I don't feel like I'm going
to be voted off anytime soon.
>> I think it will be
interesting checking out tribal
council tonight, you know, just
like going there...
>> That will be fun.
>> If it goes as I think it
will, tonight, Mary's going
home.
Mikey will be completely
confused as to what happened.
And it will be me running the
show over here.
But I've been doing a lot of
running around.
I've been talking to a lot of
people, and if these people are
smart, I could see them
thinking, "He's too powerful,
he's too manipulative," and
being very leery of me.
But either way, I think on my
feet, so we'll see what happens.
>> JEFF: Behind each of you is a
torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
approach the flame, dip it in
and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
tribal council because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire, you're
still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
So let's start at the beginning.
Kathy, right off the bat, one
person from each tribe got an
immunity idol.
How did you end up with it for
your tribe?
>> I came in last, and Yau-Man
pointed out that my idol was
under the boat, so I picked it
up.
I picked it up and went, "Is
this it?"
>> JEFF: The idol you have is
only good tonight, which means
you can use it for yourself and
stay protected, or you can give
it to somebody before we vote.
So you're clear on how that
plays tonight.
>> Yes.
>> JEFF: Let's talk about the
challenge.
Chet, this challenge for you was
extremely difficult.
You were exhausted before you
got halfway out to the platform.
>> Actually, I really wasn't
exhausted.
I thought it was best to come
back in and let somebody else go
back out, because I felt I was
wasting too much time out there.
>> JEFF: With all due respect,
that's giving yourself a little
more credit than I would.
It took you forever to go back
to the beach.
>> Okay.
>> JEFF: What's going through
your head as you feel the
pressure of nine other people
going...
>> Obviously it was a lot of
pressure, but it was what it
was.
And I would have it liked to
have been better, but it wasn't.
It didn't turn out that way.
>> JEFF: Mikey B.
>> I think the most frustrating
thing about Chet struggling was,
if you're not that good of a
swimmer, why are you not making
a team move and step down?
I mean, I was really irked by
it, to be honest with you.
>> JEFF: Tracy, tell me about
camp life.
>> It's aggravating.
We have a lot of conflicts.
The older people kind of went
one way, and the younger group
kind of went the other.
And you just sort of get a
little, you know, chafed by it,
and you say, "I'm either going
to sit back and whine about it,
or I'm going to get up, and take
care of myself."
>> JEFF: Natalie, do you see
people grouping together because
they just get along better?
>> Absolutely.
I feel that some people have
been segregated, and now we have
two shelters, so clearly there
are people that get along and
people that don't get along.
>> JEFF: Alexis, two shelters?
This doesn't sound good.
>> There was a certain division,
and two shelters have been
built, one shelter housing
Tracy, Chet, and Kathy.
So yeah, I mean, there's
definitely some conflict there.
>> JEFF: Chet, you've got to be
a little concerned tonight.
There are seven people in one
shelter, and you three are
sitting over there by yourself.
>> Sure, it looks bad that it's
three against seven.
It's really out of my control at
this point.
People have to vote how they
have to vote.
>> JEFF: Erik, would you be
concerned if you were Chet?
>> I would be very, very
concerned.
I mean, he's outside of the
numbers.
He's not as physically fit.
I would be very, very, very
scared.
>> JEFF: Mary, let's talk about
alliances, or friendships that
might be alliances.
>> Sure, you can see people
going their different
directions, and alliances
forming, but I feel pretty
secure right now with my
position in the tribe and with
the people that I choose to
communicate with and be friends
with.
>> JEFF: Joel, what do you base
a vote on this early in the
game?
You barely know these people.
>> I have a conscience, I swear,
but I don't care if anybody goes
home.
I mean, I barely know these
people, and I don't put it past
a single one of them to vote me
off tonight.
It's a game of loyalty and it's
a game of deception, and anybody
can go at any time.
And you'll never know who it is.
>> JEFF: All right, on that
note, let's get to the vote.
Kathy, you have your immunity
idol.
It has to play tonight.
>> I'll keep it for myself.
>> JEFF: Kathy's immune.
You cannot vote for Kathy.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Erik, you're up.
>> Chet, you blew it with your
body, your brains, and your
heart.
That's just not acceptable to be
a teammate of mine.
>> I just went with the
majority.
I'm sorry.
>> JEFF: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol, now would be the
time to play it.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Chet.
Chet.
Two votes Chet.
Tracy.
Two votes Chet, one vote Tracy.
Mary.
Two votes Chet, one vote Tracy,
one vote Mary.
Mary.
Two votes Mary.
Tracy.
We're tied-- two votes Tracy,
two votes Chet, two votes Mary.
Mary.
That's three votes Mary, two
votes Chet, two votes Tracy.
Mary.
That's four votes Mary.
Second person voted out of
Survivor: Fans Versus
Favorites, Mary.
Based on the way the votes were
distributed, five is enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Mary, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Bye, guys.
Win this.
>> JEFF: Well, based on what I
heard tonight, Mary never saw
that coming.
Congratulations.
First tribal council, first
blindside.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Kathy, you can leave that idol
behind.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> JEFF: Next time on Survivor,
Cirie takes control of her
tribe.
>> Which side is better for me?
>> Oh, my god!
>> JEFF: The fans continue to
suffer.
>> Oh, mother of god.
>> JEFF: And it's war between
the favorites and fans.
>> If someone comes and invades
my home, I'm going to kill them.
>> I have no idea what happened.
I'm just totally blindsided.
Not even a clue that I was going
to be going home tonight.
So it kind of sucks being the
first person to go off your
tribe, but maybe they you saw me
getting too close to some
individuals and making friends
with others.
I'm definitely rooting for the
fans.
They're all very strong
individuals, and one of the fans
will definitely win this
Survivor.