>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
Favorites win reward!
...the favorites continued to
dominate the game, winning their
third challenge in a row.
>> We've got an unbelievable
bounty over here.
>> PROBST: Ozzy found the hidden
immunity idol on Exile Island.
>> I found the idol!
>> PROBST: And he replaced it
with a fake one as a decoy.
>> Do your job now, buddy.
>> PROBST: At Airai, Chet's
laziness dragged down the tribe.
>> I don't feel like Chet really
wants to carry his weight.
Dude, like, either pick it up or
go home.
>> PROBST: And after another
Malakal victory in the immunity
challenge...
Favorites win immunity!
...Chet was Airai's obvious
target.
>> My mind is just spinning,
just the fact that he's still
here.
Chet is not in this game right
now.
He's a physical and mental
liability, and he's horrible for
morale around camp.
>> PROBST: But in order to save
her alliance, Tracy challenged
Joel...
>> Why you letting him call the
shots right now?
>> Am I letting him?
I don't know.
>> Yeah, you're freaking just
following like...
>> No, I think...
>> Like a herd of cattle down
the road.
>> PROBST: ...and turned his
attention toward Mikey B.
>> Mike's going to take you down
the next chance he gets because
of what you did to Mary.
>> I think he will, absolutely.
>> Okay, so this is his next
chance.
>> PROBST: At tribal council,
Jason made a plea to keep the
tribe strong and get rid of
Chet.
>> We have lost four of six
challenges.
Just take a moment to really
think about who we keep on the
island and who we let go.
>> PROBST: In the end...
Mike.
...Mikey B. was blindsided, and
Joel got rid of his biggest
rival.
Mike, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Good night.
>> Tonight, walking into tribal
council, I was hoping that our
tribe would make the right
decision to vote out Chet, the
weakest member of our tribe.
But unfortunately, that didn't
happen.
I'm definitely bummed that
Mikey's gone.
We need a physically strong
tribe.
I have a bad feeling that we're
just going to keep losing and
losing and losing, and I feel
that the tribe I'm in is not the
tribe I want to be in.
>> Another one bites the dust,
and it wasn't us.
>> Three outcasts prevailing.
>> Just for now.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
( theme song playing )
>> Oh, Chuckie.
>> Oh, Charlie.
>> It's about that time.
>> I'm ready for Chuckie, baby.
>> All right, let's do it.
>> Everybody is all excited to
eat Charlie the chicken.
But you know, we're ready.
We're hungry.
>> I'm worried more about my
fingers getting chopped off.
>> Yeah, just don't chop hand.
>> Yeah, I'll hold it.
You chop.
>> I guess Ozzy's going to kill
the chicken.
Ah!
I mean, it's no... I work in
surgery, so it's not a big deal
to me.
But I just don't want to see a
dead, bloody chicken flapping
everywhere.
>> Just lay him down like this.
>> Good night, baby.
>> Good night, buddy.
Good night.
Sleep good.
>> One, two, three.
>> Okay.
>> Ah, he's bloody!
>> Oh, Charlie!
>> I know.
>> Oh, Charlie.
Let's go get some wood to cook
him.
>> We're having chicken tonight.
>> After the challenge, I went
to Exile Island, and I found the
hidden immunity idol.
It's awesome.
So after we killed the chicken,
I was slick enough that I was
able to hide the immunity idol
before anyone could suspect
otherwise.
At this point, I don't think I'm
going to show anyone the idol,
but I totally trust James.
And I think I can trust Amanda.
And I know I can trust Parvati.
Don't tell anyone, but I told
James I found the idol.
>> You did?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my God!
Ozzy told me he had the immunity
idol, and he told me, James, and
Parv.
>> No.
>> Okay, good.
>> So it's in our little four
clique, and I think it's going
to stay in our little four
clique.
So we're like the powerhouse
right now.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Favorites getting your first
look at the new fan tribe.
Mikey B. voted out at the last
tribal council.
Figure after 12 days of
competing against each other,
it's time you got to know each
other.
Drop your buffs.
We are switching tribes.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: There are seven white
stones and one colored stone.
One is purple, one is orange.
For this tribe, if you grab
purple, you will be a captain.
Please don't look.
Fans, one orange stone.
If you grab orange, you're the
captain.
Don't look.
All right, everybody put your
palms up.
Three, two, one, reveal.
Natalie, Ozzy, two captains.
Take your spot over here.
Ozzy is the captain for the new
Malakal, Natalie the captain for
the new Airai tribe.
You can choose a man or a woman,
but you must choose somebody
from the opposite tribe.
So you are choosing a favorite.
>> James.
>> PROBST: James joins Natalie,
the first choice in the school-
yard pick.
Say hello to your new tribe
mate.
>> Hey, baby.
>> PROBST: Ozzy, your choice.
You're choosing a fan.
>> Troy.
>> PROBST: Who?
>> Troy-- Joel
>> Joel.
>> PROBST: Joel.
Good enough.
>> PROBST: Both big guys are
taken first.
Joel joins Ozzy on the Malakal
tribe.
James, it is now your choice.
You are now choosing a fan.
>> Alexis.
>> PROBST: Alexis joins Natalie
and James on the Airai tribe.
Joel, your choice.
You are choosing a favorite to
join you and Ozzy.
>> Amanda.
>> PROBST: Amanda joins Ozzy and
Joel on the Malakal tribe.
Alexis, your choice.
>> Jonathan.
>> PROBST: Alexis chooses
Jonathan Penner.
>> You sure?
>> PROBST: Amanda.
>> I'm going to go with Erik.
>> PROBST: Erik joins the
Malakal tribe.
Penner.
>> I got to pick blue.
I don't know his name.
>> PROBST: Jason joins the new
Airai tribe.
Erik, your choice.
>> We're going to pick Ami.
>> PROBST: Ami joins the Malakal
tribe.
>> Good to meet you.
>> Good to meet you too.
>> PROBST: Jason, your choice.
You're choosing a favorite.
>> I'm going to take Poverty.
>> Parvati.
>> Parvati, Parvati.
>> Ah, you didn't even know her
name.
>> I'll learn your name.
I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: It took me a while
too, Jason.
Ami, your choice, you're picking
a fan.
>> Tracy.
>> PROBST: Tracy joins the
Malakal Tribe.
Parvati, your choice.
>> All right, we're going to
take KB.
Sorry, Chet.
>> PROBST: Kathy joins the new
Airai Tribe.
Tracy, you're choosing a
favorite.
One of two choices.
>> All right, Cirie.
>> Sorry, girl.
>> That's okay.
I'm good.
>> PROBST: Kathy, it is your
choice.
It's been made for you.
>> Eliza.
>> PROBST: Eliza...
>> Yay, guys.
>> PROBST: ...joins the new
Airai Tribe.
Chet grabs his stuff and joins
the new Malakal Tribe.
>> Chety's here.
Chety's here.
>> PROBST: Malakal, here are
your buffs.
Airai, here are your buffs.
Put them on.
Suit up.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: We are no longer
tribes of fans versus favorites.
We are now Malakal versus Airai.
You guys ready to get to your
first challenge as new tribes?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's challenge, both tribes
will divide into pairs.
Those pairs will be harnessed
together.
Each round, starting at opposite
ends of the course, a pair from
one tribe will chase a pair from
the other tribe, attempting to
grab a flag off their back.
Each time you get a flag, you
score a point for your tribe.
If you don't grab a flag within
one minute, the other tribe
scores a point.
So it's even chances of scoring
for both tribes.
First tribe to score three
points wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes!
>> Tell me it's food.
>> What is it?
>> PROBST: It's a little "get to
know you" home barbecue.
>> Yes!
Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Steak, sausage, some
veggies, some spices, and wine.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: And because we want
you guys to have a little time
to get to know each other, no
Exile Island today.
>> Oh, nice.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> Yeah, yeah!
>> PROBST: I'll give you a
minute to figure out your pairs.
We'll get started.
All right, Malakal won the rock,
paper, scissor.
You've decided to be the
chasers.
In the first round, Erik and
Ozzy will be chasing after Kathy
and Natalie.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go get them.
>> PROBST: Ozzy and Erik cutting
right through the middle of the
course.
Natalie and Kathy got to get a
move on it.
>> You got it, you got it.
>> PROBST: Ozzy making ground.
Ozzy grabs Kathy's flag!
Malakal leads one-zip.
>> Beautiful.
>> PROBST: Now we're going to
alternate.
This time Airai will be doing
the chasing.
Parvati and Eliza will be
chasing Chet and Joel.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Eliza and Parvati, Eliza and
Parvati have them cornered.
Joel and Chet escape.
The race is on.
You have one minute to catch
him, or Joel and Chet will score
for their tribe.
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Eliza getting very
close, dragging Parvati behind
her.
30 seconds left.
Eliza grabs the flag from Chet.
Parvati and Eliza score the
first point for Airai!
You all right?
>> PROBST: Next round, it will
be Ami and Amanda chasing James
and Jason.
Tied 1-1, playing to three.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Ami and Amanda trying to catch
James and Jason.
They got one minute to do it.
Ami hops over, just misses a
shot at Jason.
>> Hold them up, guys.
Hold them up.
>> PROBST: Ami's hurt, still
hanging in there.
>> Go, go!
>> Get him!
>> PROBST: Oh, Jason tied up!
Ami has a shot at it!
Trying to get it!
Ami has Jason's flag!
Malakal leads 2-1.
Here we go, next round.
Jonathan Penner and Alexis
chasing after Cirie and Tracy.
Malakal leads 2-1.
If Cirie and Tracy can avoid
being caught, Malakal wins
reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Penner and Alexis out of the
gate quickly.
They have one minute to catch
Tracy and Cirie.
Otherwise, Malakal wins reward.
Penner dragging Alexis.
Cirie and Tracy doing a good
job, staying away.
Cirie dragging Tracy.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: 30 seconds left.
Penner reaches for the flag,
can't get it!
Alexis grabs the flag off Cirie.
We are tied 2-2.
Our injury tally so far-- Penner
has a busted up knee, Parvati
has a busted up lip, Ami has a
tweaked knee.
Next round, Airai is putting up
Parvati and Eliza.
Malakal is putting up Chet and
Joel.
We're tied 2-2.
We're playing to three.
Chet and Joel must catch Parvati
and Eliza to win reward.
Otherwise, Airai wins reward.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
>> You got them.
>> PROBST: Go!
Parvati and Eliza just have to
avoid Joel and Chet for 60
seconds, and they'll have
steaks, sausage, wine and
fixings.
>> Go through, Chet.
Follow them.
>> PROBST: Joel and Chet have
got to catch Parvati and Eliza
in order to win this game.
Joel's got them cornered, just
misses the flag.
Parvati and Eliza are alive.
Joel trying to drag Chet, takes
a hard fall!
>> Come on, Chet!
>> PROBST: Keep moving!
30 seconds!
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Joel getting
frustrated.
Parvati and Eliza have 15 more
seconds to avoid being caught...
>> Get up, let's go!
>> PROBST: ...for a big barbecue
reward!
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Joel and Chet cannot catch
Parvati and Eliza!
Airai wins reward!
>> PROBST: All right, Airai wins
the first challenge as new
tribes.
Nice work.
( applause )
Big reward-- steak, veggies,
some wine to celebrate.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> PROBST: Malakal, got nothing
for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> We've got a... back there,
there's a giant cave.
I'll show you guys that.
>> Oh, cool.
Even more than what we have.
>> And then we have the
chickens.
>> I'm not good about losing.
I know that's where my temper
gets to me.
And I'm still decompressing.
Maybe this is poetic justice in
some form, because I chose to
get rid of Mikey versus Chet.
And now here I end up with Chet
again on my tribe, who's
probably the weakest of both the
tribes.
>> Erik, are you coming?
>> You know, there is a little
bit of irony in that.
But at the same time, it can be
good to have people around that
ultimately will be expendable.
>> Oh, my god!
>> When it rains, this is the
place to be.
>> Yeah, it's all dry here.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, this is wonderful.
>> It's ridiculously dry here.
I am so excited to be on this
tribe right now.
I like these people on this
tribe.
I mean, I got to meet Ozzy
today!
At this point, the game has
changed completely.
Now, rather than being with the
fans, I'm with some of the
favorites.
But I'm going to try and not let
that cloud my judgment.
They're still people in this
game.
>> And then we use half of it as
a blanket.
We sleep on this half, and then
we pull that up.
>> You don't understand.
We had nothing, so...
>> That's why, like, you know,
it really sucks to lose the
challenge today, but it's one
meal.
It's one nice meal.
But you know, we're going to be
eating.
I feel like we do have an
advantage because we're on the
Malakal beach, and we have all
of the things that you need to
be a strong tribe.
>> Thank God I can hug you now.
>> It's just a question of are
we going to be a strong tribe?
Chet, man, he's like a sack of
potatoes.
In the challenge, he freaking
gave up.
Like, he just... he was, like,
being dragged.
He wouldn't even stand up.
I just don't see him being a
strong competitor at all.
I don't know what's going on
with that dude, but he needs to
go.
>> Lift up.
I've always liked chickens.
I've raised chickens all my
life, so I pretty much know
everything about chickens.
They're very, you know, peaceful
animals.
They're very placid.
But, you know, they have their
own pecking order-- literally, a
pecking order-- where the
weakest one is always basically
pecked on until they're killed--
the same as pretty much in this
game of Survivor.
The weaker one is usually pecked
on until they're removed from
the tribe.
>> Then this is where our fire
is.
So... and then we made, like, a
little...
>> So this is the shelter?
>> This was Chet, mine, and
Tracy's.
We build... we had to build this
one.
This slept us three, and those
slept seven.
>> So you guys sleep on the
beach with these things jumping
all over you?
>> Yeah, it's pretty gross.
>> Wow.
>> The Airai camp is pretty much
a disaster.
The beach is not as good as our
beach.
Kathy, move that up a little,
because the tide is starting to
come up behind you.
Even though winning the food
reward of steaks and spices and
wine was great, at Malakal, we
had everything.
And here, we pretty much have
nothing.
It's definitely a downgrade in
terms of camp life.
>> I'm so happy.
It's nice to have things kind of
shaken up.
So it's good to get to know more
people.
>> Whoa!
Not good.
>> Can it get up that high that
it's going to put our fire out?
>> Yeah.
>> The water hasn't come into
your shelter, has it?
>> Not yet.
>> Oh, just to hear that
sizzling sound is great!
>> So good right now!
>> Oh, my gosh.
Here comes the water.
>> Ah!
>> No.
No, it did not.
>> No, it didn't.
It did?
No.
>> The old Airai, the setup that
they were living in was
terrible.
The waters are washing away the
fire, you know.
I'm amazed that they're still
alive, poor things.
They should be dead.
I mean, they're a bunch of
dingbats.
More wood, huh?
>> It went really deep.
>> Yeah.
Oh.
>> Well, my knee's a little
screwy.
I was on the course in the
challenge, punctured it somehow.
There was some sharp something,
went right into my muscle.
A lot of people got fat lips and
twisted knees and stuff like
that, and I found a stick, and
it went straight into my leg.
I'm gimping around like I'm
Quasimoto.
It's painfully sore.
I really tweaked the hell out of
it.
Oh.
It's not too late to suture,
right?
It's all right?
And... and... argh!
Ah!
>> A little one again.
>> Ow!
Damn it!
Ah.
It hurts!
>> Ow!
God!
It's crazy!
I'm in the middle of the
freaking jungle.
A wonderful doctor came out to
the beach and cleaned my wound
and stitched it up, and they
left me with three stitches and
a painful leg.
>> He's going to live.
>> Are you all right then?
>> Oh, I'm fine.
There could be an infection, and
it could work down towards the
joint of my knee.
So let's hope it doesn't get
worse.
>> Ozzy is amazing.
The kid can swim like crazy.
He's natural in the water.
That's just... that's just how
he was born, and there's nothing
to it other than that.
I mean, I can't compete with
him.
He's amazing.
>> We are in a really good
position over here, because I
think we have a really strong
tribe, aside from maybe one
person.
>> Yeah.
>> What are you thinking?
>> You're obviously thinking
something.
>> I'm just thinking Chet, and
then after that, between Tracy
and Cirie, which, I mean, I
don't know.
>> I'll tell you what.
If you're willing to get rid of
Cirie first, I got no problem
giving up Chet and then being
back to 3-3, calling that fair.
>> After we were out on the
water, we had a little
conversation on the beach
between mainly Joel and Ozzy,
and I kind of listened in.
And it was kind of like two
superpowers kind of discussing
terms.
>> You know, being completely
legitimate, our concern is that
there's four from the favorites
and four from the fans, and the
first one to go down to three is
kind of...
>> Screwed.
>> You know, unless something
changes.
>> Well, if we can trust each
other...
>> Unless there's some level of
trust somewhere.
I think it is, to a degree,
still fans versus favorites, but
either the favorites have to
swing a fan over to their side,
or the fans have to swing a
favorite over to their side.
Somebody's going to have to
flip.
>> So if we build our day camp
at the other end of the beach,
we can build a camp for all
eight of us to sleep together.
>> Let's do it!
>> When we woke up this morning,
it was the first priority to
find a new location for the new
shelter.
>> Is this too far?
>> No.
I mean, I'd say this is the best
place to build something.
>> Yeah, I think is...
>> To have four new people with
so much experience under their
belt, being able to point at
this and say, "We need to do
this, and we need to do this,
and this is how we did this," I
mean, it's unbelievable.
>> We need two posts.
We'll have the front this way.
>> With our new tribe, this got
erected in an hour.
The new members of Airai, I
mean, they're just on it.
They're quick.
They're making it happen.
It's getting done.
And it's brilliant.
>> It's so refreshing to have
new people here.
I know you all are sad to miss
your cave and all that, but I
can't tell you how nice it is
for us.
>> Yeah, I understand that.
>> What'd you get?
>> Oh, my god!
>> What is it?
>> A huge shark.
>> Shark!
>> Ozzy!
>> A big shark dead in the net?
>> Yeah.
That's why we have to keep the
net clean, because the sharks...
>> Ozzy!
>> It's huge, huh?
>> When I went over to the net,
I looked down, and there was
this huge white thing.
And I'm like, "Oh, my God."
>> That's, like, 40 pounds
maybe.
>> 40 pounds?
>> Yeah, 35, 40 pounds.
>> It was huge.
What am I going to do?
I'm from Montana.
We don't have sharks in Montana.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Isn't that freaky?
>> I mean, damn, Amanda, she
basically wrestled a four-foot
shark by herself.
I mean, that's pretty attractive
to a guy like me.
>> It's so juicy.
Oh, my God!
>> I'll take this over beefsteak
any time.
Best eating in over 13 days.
>> If it makes you guys feel
better, it's the best eating for
us, too.
>> That does make me feel
better.
>> That was an amazing meal.
Now we just want to kick ass.
We just want to start winning.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Ami, take back immunity.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, four
members from each tribe will
alternate throwing rocks at
ceramic tiles.
Each time you break a tile, you
release a bundle of wooden
puzzle pieces.
Once you've collected all four
bundles, three tribe members
will assemble the puzzle with
the help from a caller on top of
a tower.
The edges of each puzzle piece
must match the color of the
piece next to it, which means
black must line up with black,
purple with purple, orange with
orange.
If it doesn't line up, you don't
have it right.
First tribe to solve the puzzle
correctly wins immunity; losers,
tribal council, somebody going
home.
Give you a minute to strategize,
and we'll get started.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, guys.
>> Come on, James.
>> PROBST: Throwing rocks to
break tiles.
>> Come on, Ozzy.
>> PROBST: Ozzy connects and
breaks the first tile for
Malakal.
>> Almost, almost.
>> Come on, Tracy!
>> Come on, Tracy.
>> You got it.
>> Take your time.
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: Tracy breaks a tile
for Malakal.
Penner breaks a tile for Airai.
James smashes a tile but not
enough.
>> Oh, that sucks!
Come on!
>> PROBST: You have to
obliterate that tile to get the
rope to drop.
Erik breaks a third tile for
Malakal.
>> Keep going, keep going.
Quickly, guys, quickly.
>> PROBST: Malakal only has one
tile left to break.
>> Pick it up.
Let's pick it up.
Yes!
>> PROBST: James breaks another
tile, but it doesn't drop.
Got to smash all the way
through.
Jason breaks a tile for Airai.
>> Come on, smash those, smash
those, quickly, guys, quickly.
>> PROBST: Erik drops the fourth
tile for Malakal.
>> Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry,
hurry.
>> Bull!
We say bull, bull, bull!
>> PROBST: Penner, you got the
same tiles, the same ropes.
>> They've got a knot we've got
to untie.
Here, let me untie it.
>> Purple and then pink.
>> Right there, it's right
there.
Put that one in there.
>> I mean, my ass!
>> What?
>> PROBST: Airai, you need to
stop bitching and start
throwing.
>> Just hitting them as hard as
we can, Jeff.
>> There you go.
Okay, there, there.
>> PROBST: Malakal working on
their puzzle already.
>> Like that, like that, like
that.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Airai drops their
third tile.
One left.
Jason gets it down!
Airai collecting their puzzle
pieces.
>> Pull them, pull them!
Quick, quick, quick!
They're not close.
We can get this.
>> That's not it.
>> Something's wrong here.
That's not it.
>> White, white.
Just look at it.
>> PROBST: All colors much match
up along the frame and with
other pieces of tile.
>> That piece is wrong right
here.
>> No, no, it's pink right here,
pink right here.
>> We got to get the corner
pieces.
We need a yellow with an orange
on that one.
>> PROBST: Eliza calling the
shots for Airai.
>> The other way.
The white has to touch the
white.
Yeah, bottom.
>> PROBST: Chet calling the
shots for Malakal.
>> That white right there
shouldn't just, like, end that
way.
>> I think that one has to be
the corner.
Take that one and put it here,
Parv.
>> PROBST: Airai made up a lot
of time.
We are dead even right now.
>> That piece is wrong.
These black ones need to go to
that corner.
>> That piece isn't going to fit
in there.
>> No, it will.
Keep that white one there.
>> PROBST: Joel getting very
involved in this puzzle.
>> You know what, Eliza?
See if you can see the big
picture.
There's got to be a bigger
pattern to it.
>> It's a black and white
zigzag-- black on this side,
white on this side.
>> Parv, give her the one in
your hand.
Yeah, put that there.
>> Yes, now you're on to
something.
>> PROBST: Airai thinks they're
getting closer.
>> This piece here has to come
out.
Yes, take that out.
>> No, that one's right, Cirie.
>> Okay, I think we got it.
>> There we go.
That's it.
>> We're done.
>> Oh, my god, we got it.
We got it, we got it, we got it!
Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Airai wins immunity!
( cheering )
>> Comeback, baby!
>> PROBST: Airai, immunity.
( applause )
Nobody going home.
Malakal, tribal council tonight.
One of you will be voted out.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
I'll see you at tribal.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> We lost the challenge, and
for me, this is what, five, six
losses in a row?
I mean, I stopped counting.
>> Oh!
>> At this point, I don't know
if it can be a fans versus
favorites anymore, unless we
want to really just keep losing.
So...
>> Yeah.
>> I could care less about how
the numbers dwindle away.
>> I really could care less as
well.
I think Chet's our priority.
>> Just doing the right thing,
and the right thing is to get
rid of the weak.
This game is a game for strong
people, and we need to keep it
that way.
I don't think I've ever, in my
life, interacted with somebody
that is so just spineless.
>> Clean your coop out later.
>> It's almost like he's a wet
rag or a ball of goo.
There's absolutely zero honor
whatsoever in keeping somebody
like that on our team.
I mean, if you went back to
medieval times, I think we'd
kill him ourselves.
You can only ever play the hand
you're dealt, right, Oz?
>> Yeah.
>> Play it to the best of your
ability and get rid of the cards
that aren't working for you, and
I think we got a couple cards
that aren't working for us.
>> What do you think?
>> Yeah?
>> That's my thought.
>> I know.
>> You want a drink of this?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> I think we should make our
team the strongest.
>> I think so, too.
I definitely think so.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Okay.
>> Erik seems to think that we
should get rid of the weaker
players in the tribe, which
would be fine with me, except
I'm included in the weaker tribe
members.
>> We lost that challenge today
because of him.
>> See, I can't see...
>> I could see it, and you girls
were right.
He could have moved on, but he
was like, "Get it out of there!
Get it out of there!"
Joel, it was his fault today.
>> Chet is viewed as one of the
weaker players, but at the same
time, Joel didn't help his own
team win, and he didn't help us
win today.
>> Right now, I have to convince
Ozzy and Amanda that Joel is a
bigger threat for us than Chet
is.
>> ...then we'll have Joel.
We'll still have the numbers.
We'll be able to win reward.
We'll be able to decide who to
send to Exile.
>> You think Joel is really that
great helping us win?
He didn't help us win today.
He didn't hit one tile.
Big as he is...
>> That's true.
>> ...he should have hit
something.
Tracy is, like, this big and hit
more tiles than he did.
>> I know.
>> He didn't do nothing but
screw us up in the puzzle.
>> Like, I mean, he's still,
like, a mover and a shaker.
Chet's nothing and a nothing.
>> But Joel is already playing
the game.
Chet ain't really into playing
the game like that.
There are so many pluses for
getting rid of Joel, and Chet is
just like a pawn.
We can use Chet for whatever we
need whenever we need.
>> That's true.
>> Joel you can't do that with.
>> That makes sense.
This is an incredibly important
vote tonight.
We are at a crossroads.
We are at a point where we need
to decide how we're going to
approach the rest of the game.
Chet, in challenges, he is a
waste of space.
On the other hand, Joel wants to
win challenges, but Joel wants
to win the game really bad, and
Joel is dangerous.
It's a hard decision.
>> PROBST: So let's talk about
the switch.
Ozzy, you and Natalie were
selected as captains.
Natalie had the first choice,
immediately took James.
You countered with Joel.
Was that to match up size for
size?
>> Yeah.
It just seemed like the logical
choice at the time to try and
match James's strength with
Joel's.
>> PROBST: On the flip side,
Chet, you really weren't even
picked.
You were left over and ended up
on this tribe.
Does that work on your psyche at
all about where you fit in this
game?
>> Um, you know, I felt like I
was in trouble from day one in
this game, but I'm still sitting
here.
And of course, it's not the
greatest to be picked last, but
that was the group of people I
wanted to end up with, whether
they chose me or whether I went
there by default, so I was very
happy with the results, no
matter what.
>> PROBST: Tracy, let's talk
about the challenge where you
were dragging each other through
the mud.
It was your first time together
as a new group.
What do you think?
>> I think that watching Joel
and Chet, if there had just been
a smidgen of communication for
the guy he was dragging around
behind him, then we almost would
have had it.
If somebody with you can't walk
or gets their head whopped
against a board and they can't
see, putting your feet down and
pulling like a Clydesdale, you
know, is just not going to get
it done.
>> PROBST: Joel, obviously,
Tracy's talking about you and
the way you were dragging Chet
around like he was a bundle of
bananas.
>> Yeah.
What do you want me to say?
There was communication.
If I was going under, I said,
"Under."
If I was going through, I said,
"Through."
Don't shake your head.
If I was going over, I said,
"Over."
If he couldn't hear me because
there was mud in his ears from
being dragged through it, it's
not my fault.
>> PROBST: Chet, what was your
experience being the one behind,
being dragged?
>> First off, I felt like I was
harnessed to a Mack truck and
drug through the forest.
And when somebody is making up
their mind in a split second,
you do end up getting smashed
into posts.
And there wasn't as much
communication in the last aspect
of that challenge for us as
there was in the beginning for
us.
>> PROBST: Erik, tonight's vote,
is this about keeping a tribe
strong so we can win in
challenges, or is it four fans,
four favorites, somebody's going
to win out?
>> When you bring the two groups
together, there is that initial
thought, the fans versus the
favorites still.
But at this point, I think most
of us are looking at this as we
just need to stay strong.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Erik, you're up.
>> I'm voting for Chet tonight.
We want to stay strong as a
tribe, and take it easy.
>> This is because you called me
weak one too many times.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Joel.
Chet.
One vote Joel, one vote Chet.
Two votes Chet, one vote Joel.
Joel.
Two vote Joel, two votes Chet.
That's three votes Joel, two
votes Chet.
Joel.
That's four votes Joel, two
votes Chet.
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Fans vs. Favorites,
Joel.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Hey, big guy.
>> PROBST: Joel, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Well, tonight's vote
established what is important to
this tribe, and clearly,
physical strength, not at the
top of the list.
Certainly caught Joel by
surprise.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, Ami questions her
loyalty to the favorites.
>> I'm really conflicted right
now.
>> PROBST: On Exile Island,
Jason makes a puzzling
discovery.
>> This is really good for me.
>> PROBST: And Jonathan battles
an infection.
>> An infection that goes into
your blood stream is potentially
fatal.
>> The tribe picked Chet over
me-- a little bit humiliating,
insulting.
Wow.
I don't understand why you would
want to keep somebody like Chet.
It's just very, very confusing.
I'm angry.
I mean, I think I'd like to
wring a couple people's necks
right now, but I'm stunned.
I'm stunned.