>> JEFF PROBST: Previously,
on Survivor:
(gorilla grunting)
>> Obviously, Bob and I know
that our numbers are up.
>> PROBST: Outnumbered five to
two, Bob and Corinne hatched a
plan.
Step one: Bob made another fake
hidden immunity idol.
>> That would fool me.
>> PROBST: In fact, it looked
almost as good as the real idol
Sugar has had for most of the
game.
>> Thank God.
>> PROBST: Step two: Corinne
told Kenny she had an idol and
convinced him to flip.
>> Who are you guys gonna take
out?
>> We're taking out Matty.
>> PROBST: Step three: Bob
showed the idol to Crystal, and
together, they also agreed to
vote out Matty.
Then Kenny changed the plan by
ordering Crystal to vote for
Corinne.
>> You have to vote for Corinne.
>> Okay.
>> If this plan works out, I'll
be the biggest strategist in
Survivor history.
>> PROBST: Kenny's new plan
hinged on Corinne playing the
idol, but she couldn't because
it was fake.
So Corinne got the boot.
Matty received three votes and
was fuming.
Will Kenny's latest strategic
move come back to bite him?
Six are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> The vote tonight was four
votes for Corinne and three
votes for me.
And I believe that tonight I got
a vote from Kenny, and he wants
me out of the game.
You were voting out Corinne
tonight.
Why did you put down my name?
>> Because they had the immunity
idol.
I thought it was the real one.
>> Don't lie, bro.
That's what you're doing.
>> Once I got back from camp,
Matty was super mad at me.
I voted for him, and that was
strategically a move to gain me
jury votes in the final three.
I have been calling the shots
since day one out here, you
know?
I am the mastermind behind
everything going on.
Both of you, just listen to my
story.
>> I started getting an earload
of crap from Kenny, you know,
why he did what he did, and I
didn't even want to hear it from
him, you know?
Don't lie, Kenny.
Kenny's playing a game.
He's a mastermind.
And I'm on to him.
>> Don't worry. Don't worry.
I really like Matty, but he's a
huge physical threat.
I have a strong alliance with
Kenny and Crystal, and that's
the best alliance I've had in
the whole entire game.
>> He's put your name down.
>> Yeah, exactly.
And I still ain't put his name
down yet.
I owe him, and I'm letting both
y'all know, I owe him.
I'm really regretting not
writing Matty's name down
tonight, which is probably the
stupidest move that I've made in
this game so far.
Hopefully, Matty doesn't win
immunity at the next challenge,
and Matty needs to go.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> No.
(sighs)
It's fake.
>> So you guys did lie to me.
And now my game is messed up.
>> I feel horrible about pulling
Kenny in... uh, who's now, he's
in a real predicament, and it's
my fault.
>> Okay. Are you... are you
genuinely saying that, or are
you just lying to me again?
>> Bob offered to give me the
immunity necklace.
I made him feel sorry for me.
This is a huge power play.
>> Um, I feel horrible about it.
I made Kenny a promise that I
wouldn't play him as a fool and
that I owe him something, and I
want to be, you know, a man of
my word.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will race out
into the swamp through a
series of obstacles and retrieve
a ball.
You'll then race back to the
start, toss the ball into a net,
then you head back out.
First person to get three balls
in their net wins reward.
The winner will be flown via
helicopter to Loango National
Park, where you will visit a
gorilla sanctuary sponsored by
Africa's Eden.
This is a great opportunity to
see, up close and personal,
these fascinating animals.
You will then enjoy a nice meal,
a good night's sleep, with a bed
and a shower.
You'll return to camp in the
morning.
In addition, the winner of this
challenge has the power to send
one person to Exile Island.
Worth playing for?
All right, we'll draw for spots,
we'll get started.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready...
Go!
Into the swamp...
through the net...
>> Ow!
>> PROBST: Kenny to his station
first.
Matty right behind.
Bob now working on his.
Matty quickly has his ball and
is heading back.
Kenny has his first ball,
heading back.
Bob's heading back.
Once you get it in the net, head
back out and do it again.
Bob now back, taking a shot.
Got to get it in the net before
you can head back out.
Matty has his first ball in.
Heading back out.
Kenny has his first ball in.
Kenny heading back out.
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: Bob gets one in the
net.
Matty through the course and now
heading back with his second
ball.
All three guys have hit their
shots.
The women have yet to make one.
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: Matty taking aim.
Just misses.
Kenny now back with his second
ball.
Bob not panicking, not rushing.
Matty drills his second one.
Bob, with one shot, drills his
second ball.
Kenny hits his second one.
He's heading out.
It is Matty, Bob, Kenny heading
out for their third and final
ball.
Matty with a big advantage in
time.
Bob now getting in on it.
It is Matty, Bob, and Kenny.
First one to get their ball in
the net wins reward.
Kenny just misses.
Matty just misses.
Bob scores!
Bob wins reward!
>> Good going, Bob.
>> Oh, it's all good.
(indistinct chatter)
>> (grunts)
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Bob, come on over.
Your reward is pretty nice.
Do a little gorilla watching,
nice meal, good night's sleep in
a bed.
An adventure like this is always
more fun if you can share it.
Choose one person to go with you
on this reward.
Crystal.
>> Oh, thank you!
>> PROBST: Crystal gonna join
Bob for a nice reward.
Two's fun; three's a party.
Pick one other person to go with
you.
>> Kenny.
>> PROBST: Without hesitating,
Bob chooses Kenny.
>> The way I'm playing the game
right now is, I need Crystal and
Kenny to work with me.
Because I am trying to play for
all the marbles in the pot.
>> PROBST: All right, Bob, one
more big decision.
You have three people left.
One of them is going to Exile
Island.
>> Miss Q can go.
Susie Q.
>> PROBST: Susie Q, Exile Island
awaits you.
Grab your stuff.
>> I'm right here.
>> PROBST: You will return in
time for the next immunity
challenge.
Straight out this way.
(indistinct talking)
Sugar, Matty, got nothing for
you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Bye. Have fun.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Crystal and Kenny drive me
nuts.
They've spent way too long in
this game.
My goal with Sugar is to get her
to align with me and vote Kenny
and Crystal out.
>> PROBST: Bob, Crystal, Kenny,
helicopter coming in.
Have a great time.
Head on out.
♪ ♪
(trumpets)
>> Oh, my God, this is my first
time in a helicopter, and, yeah,
I was enjoying it.
Looking down you see nothing but
pure jungle and savanna.
It's-it's... it really is Eden
out here.
(speaking in native language)
>> Oh, my God.
>> We walk into this hut and the
first thing, of course, we see
on the table is food.
You have your fresh mango, your
fresh watermelon, your salami,
your cheese, your olives, your
tomatoes.
>> Ooh, ooh!
>> These are good.
>> Thank you, guys, for joining
me.
>> Thank you.
>> Cheers.
>> I wish I could have brought
everybody.
>> I think if Matty doesn't win
tomorrow, you know, that would
be a good thing.
>> I hope the next move is
Matty because if it's not
Matty, it's going to be one of
us.
>> Can we get Sugar on board
with that?
It would be nice if we could
take Matty out, and it's nice
that I think I have won the
confidence of Crystal and Kenny.
And I think my integrity has
stepped in here and is working.
Kenny believes I will give him
the immunity if I win it, and
the reason he believes me, I
think, is, because I do have
integrity.
>> I mean, if you win immunity,
I could take a risk.
You don't have to give it to me
the first time.
But...
>> If I don't give it to you
the first time, I'm not a man
of my word, right?
>> Yeah, that's true.
>> Uh, but if you want to...
You want to analyze and get me
off the hook.
Originally, I told you, I would
give it to you right away.
I think the best thing is for
you to make the decision.
>> Yeah, and I'll be like,
"I think you should keep it
tonight, Bob."
Or I'll say, "I think that I'm
in danger."
>> This is the plan: at the
next Tribal, I'll be wearing
the necklace I haven't won yet,
and if Kenny feels that he
needs it, and if he wants it,
I will give it to him.
If he thinks it's better off
protecting me, he'll say,
"No, keep it."
>> I think all of us look so
dirty.
I hope they're going to let us
take a shower and get cleaned
up before we go.
>> See the gorillas?
>> Mmm.
>> I'm so excited.
To take a shower was
invigorating.
We had soap and towels and
washcloths.
And put on some fresh clothes,
and we were just like, "Wow,
you smell so good."
>> Oh, man!
>> It was pretty cool.
>> Wow, Bob.
>> A big improvement.
>> I know.
>> The green does kind of look
good on you, too.
>> It does.
>> It's even got pockets.
>> Hey, guys.
>> Hi.
>> Welcome to Mbenge, the
Gorilla Project.
>> Nice to meet you.
I'm Bob.
>> After we cleaned up, some
rangers came in and spoke to us
about the Gorilla Project.
It's called Africa's Eden.
>> So, we're a sanctuary and
a rehabilitation center.
>> So, the rangers explained
everything about gorillas.
They said they were really in
danger because of people
poaching them in Africa, getting
gorilla meat, and what's left
is baby orphaned gorillas, and
they have nowhere to go.
>> We walked down to an
observation platform, and we
sat there for quite some time,
just sort of getting them used
to us.
And then Mbakai, the large
silverback gorilla, stepped out.
His head is enormous.
We were 25 feet from him.
He was right there.
I'm not usually spiritual, but
there was a feeling like there
was a connection between these
great apes and myself, how they
were looking at us, and we were
looking at them.
And it just...
It did sort of rock my soul.
>> Coming to Exile, I know that
Sugar has the idol, so I went
ahead and took my chances and
just enjoyed the comfort and the
fruit just to get away from the
whole game.
People back at Nobag have
no idea what they're missing.
It was pretty easy choosing the
comfort, actually.
But the one great thing about
being at Exile is it takes you
away from the game.
You can just step away and say,
"I don't have to think about
anything right now."
I think I'm going to have to
change it from "Sugar Shack" to
"Susie Shack."
>> Well, we went on a cool
reward and they didn't get to do
anything.
>> I've been gunning for
Crystal and Kenny this entire
game.
>> Really?
>> Yeah, really.
>> Well, I'll tell you what.
You better win that thing
tomorrow because you're the
biggest threat now.
I wouldn't want to be Matty
right now because he knows
he's next.
If it's not Bob, who is it?
In my alliance with Kenny and
Crystal...
>> It is your alliance.
>> It's me and Kenny and
Crystal.
>> So now you're choosing them
as your alliance?
Brilliant thinking.
You're the evil three.
>> We're not the evil three,
dude.
>> I don't know, man.
>> It's mostly with me and
Kenny.
Unless, you know, he could
totally be taking me for a ride.
>> He is taking you for a ride
because his main alliance is
Crystal.
I know for 1,000%.
>> I'm sure Kenny is probably
lying to me, but Matty is the
stronger physical threat, so
I don't know who to believe.
I don't know who to turn to.
I'm pretty sure you and Bob
will win.
>> Well, you have the idol.
>> Nobody's going to vote for
you.
>> We'll see.
>> Not with having the idol.
>> Oh, Matty.
I'm certainly not going to
give Matty my idol.
Screw that.
At this point, I'm using my
idol to make sure I'm in the
final five.
>> If Bob takes the next
immunity challenge, they're
voting for me.
>> I would say that's accurate.
>> My status now is I'm
basically on my own.
And I'm not getting any help
from anybody, and if I don't win
the next immunity challenge,
I think I'm packing up my bags
and going home.
>> Yay!
Was it the best ever?
>> Yes.
>> All right, tell us about it.
>> Look at this.
>> Your shirt is clean?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, my God.
Let me wear it.
>> This is...
The green is a lot.
>> It's cool that Bob went on
the experience, but he chose
Kenny and Crystal, which was
so annoying and frustrating to
me because those two just...
I don't know.
I'm having a hard time with
those two still.
>> I can feel it, Matty, that
you're, like, mad at me.
So, I don't know why you're
trying to hide it.
>> I never voted for you.
You said we were going to the
end together, Kenny.
>> There's no reason to be
upset.
>> I have good reason.
My name was written down three
times here.
>> My name's been written down
eight, one of them by you.
You still, to this day, say
"Crystal, thank you for not
writing my name down."
>> My name has been written
down seven times already.
>> I don't care.
>> Think about that.
>> Hey, Kenny, don't talk about
it anymore, okay, bro?
>> No, I'm mad.
Matty is super paranoid.
Ever since his name was written
down.
It was a strategic move on my
part, but...
It's a game.
People write down names.
>> Let him be scared.
Karma's a bitch in this game.
Right now I'm throwing the stink
on Matty, so everybody else can
smell it and write his name
down.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Because you and Sue are like
that.
>> I am like that with Sue.
I like Sue.
I like spending time with Sue
out here.
I don't trust her.
>> You can look me in the eye
and say you don't trust Sue.
>> I don't trust Sue.
>> You're lying.
>> What?
>> You've changed, and it's not
for the good.
But if you (blip) me and Kenny
over, karma is a bitch.
>> Why are you getting mad at
me?
I didn't do anything.
>> Because me and Kenny have
been there for you from day
one.
>> What do you mean?
What do you want from me?
>> I don't want anything from
you.
I don't want anything from you.
>> I have no idea what's
happening right now.
Crystal is going off on Matty
for no reason, and I've already
seen Kenny go off on Matty, and
Matty doesn't deserve to be
yelled at.
>> What am I doing wrong,
Crystal?
>> Keep doing what you're doing.
But where did this come from?
>> Matty is right, I think,
that Crystal and Kenny have
been in this together from the
beginning and they just take
out whoever they want.
Kenny acts like he's this weak,
little meager guy, and he spins
all these lies, and Crystal is
just a big bully.
This is the thing.
They're not good people.
I'm starting to see that about
Kenny, and I know that about
Crystal.
>> Do you really, or you just...
I don't know what's going on.
>> I don't, either, but now I
see that they're not, like...
Why would they kick you when
you're down?
It feels like they're just
going off on you when you know
you're going.
But you're not going.
>> Why don't I just...
>> You're not going to go.
Okay?
>> Well, what do we do?
>> You, me, Bob, and Sue.
I have to talk to Bob because
I know Bob better than anybody
else.
At this point.
>> Sugar, are you truthful?
>> I am not...
>> If Sugar really is telling
me the truth, I have hope, and I
could play this game.
I might have to go to the end
with Bob, and Bob will
dominate, but least good will
prevail.
>> It's either me and you
guys or you guys and Sue.
>> Who do we take out first,
then, if you're being serious?
>> Crystal.
Crystal goes first.
>> This is just intense.
I'm just praying that I can
find the strength to...
finish.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Susie,
returning from Exile Island.
>> It was a good time.
It was a good time.
>> PROBST: Welcome back.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to
get to today's immunity
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Bob, I will take back the
necklace.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, on my
"go," you will study the
features of a Gabonese mask.
You will then grab a bag of mask
pieces and make your way
through a series of obstacles
to a station where you will
find a second blank mask.
You will then use those pieces
to fill in the missing features.
One more thing: you will be
blindfolded.
First person to collect all
three bags and successfully
recreate the mask wins
immunity-- guaranteed a one in
what, Kenny?
>> One in five chance of
winning a million dollars.
>> PROBST: There you go.
Losers, Tribal Council, where
somebody will be voted out of
this game.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
All right, we'll get started.
Here we go.
Other side, Sugar, other side.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You will use your hands to study
that mask.
Or, if you decide to, you can
head out right away.
It is up to you.
Matty quickly out to a lead.
Matty at his station first, got
his first bag, and he's heading
back.
Not going to work on it one bag
at a time.
Kenny back with his first bag
of pieces.
Bob is back.
Sugar, Bob, Kenny are all going
to start working on recreating
the mask.
Matty's going to go get all of
his pieces at once.
Crystal.
>> Yes?
>> PROBST: You are off the
course.
>> Oh, shoot.
>> PROBST: You are in the wrong
lane.
You're completely off track.
You got to get back on the
course and find your lane.
Matty coming back with his
second bag of pieces, while
Kenny, Bob, Sugar, and Susie
start working with their first
bag of facial features.
Crystal, up over a hitching
post, heading the right way.
In the wrong lane.
Matty heading back for his
third and final bag.
Bob is heading back, looking
for his second bag.
Crystal once again off the
course.
Crystal back on the course.
Matty coming back with that
third bag.
Everybody else so close and
yet so far away when you cannot
see.
Matty now back with all three
bags of the facial features.
Matty now going to start
working on his mask.
Kenny heading back now, looking
for that second bag.
Bob is back with his second bag.
Crystal, miraculously, is
almost there.
Crystal has arrived with her
first bag.
Kenny takes a header into a
pole.
Even the king can get injured
in this challenge.
Everybody working on their mask
now.
Bob now heading back for his
third and final bag.
Susie heading back for her
second bag.
(Bob groans, chuckles)
Bob took a header into a
station.
Susie is off the course.
Bob heading back with that
third and final bag.
Matty going to head back to
check his mask again, while Bob
is back with that third and
final bag.
>> I think I have it.
>> PROBST: Bob thinks he has it.
Bob does not have it.
Matty now coming back after
checking that mask.
Bob making a lot of changes.
Kenny still working on his mask.
He has all three bags.
The question now is, "Do I have
the right pieces?"
Crystal not giving up,
continues to fight in this
challenge.
Susie trying to find the course.
>> I think I have it, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Kenny thinks he has
it.
Kenny is wrong.
Kenny going to head back to
check his mask again.
Matty very close.
Bob is almost there.
Big immunity on the line.
>> I'll just try that.
>> PROBST: Bob thinks he has it.
Bob is right!
Bob wins immunity!
Four straight challenges.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Bob, come on over.
Once again, immunity is yours.
Turn around, brother.
Once again, Bob is safe at
Tribal Council.
After 36 long days, Tribal
Council tonight.
One of you will be going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> Four challenges in a row.
I'm 57 years old.
It felt real good.
Been a good run at four.
I never would have guessed that.
>> Bob promised me that if he
won the immunity necklace that
he'll give it to me.
Now, it's up to Bob, you know.
Actions do speak louder than
words, and I can only wait to
see what he does tonight.
>> I know you want to get rid
of Matty.
But we get rid of Matty tonight,
there's a chance Bob lied to me
and won't give me the necklace
next time.
So I'm going to tell Bob to
give me the necklace tonight.
And we got to vote for Bob.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Is that okay?
>> I'm cool with that.
>> Who would've thought Bob
would be winning all these
challenges?
But he has been.
We should have got rid of him
when we had the chance, but we
kept him in because everybody
hated Randy.
And now we're paying for it.
He's too dangerous at this
point.
None of us has the chance to
make it to the final three.
>> Okay.
In all honesty, I would like
to take out Matty, but if it's
Bob's name we're going with
tonight, Bob it is.
As long as it's not Crystal,
I'm fine.
>> Hmm?
Why?
Why would you be scared?
>> I don't know.
Bob made a deal with me, you
know.
He's going to give me that
immunity necklace if he wins.
If he doesn't, he'll look
really bad in front of
everybody.
If he does, he'll look good in
front of everybody, and he'll go
home.
So lose-lose situation for him.
>> Why would they blindside you?
We're going to take Matty out.
Why would you feel nervous?
>> 'Cause I'm with you.
There might be the four still.
>> Okay, okay.
We'll talk... we'll talk.
We'll talk about it.
Let's find out who's voting
for who?
>> What?
>> Hey, guys.
>> Kenny has come up with this
elaborate plan to hoax Bob out
of his necklace.
If Bob were to give Kenny the
necklace, then everybody would
vote for Bob because they want
to keep their five alliance.
I don't want to be aligned with
all those guys.
I want to be aligned with the
good guys.
Crystal and Kenny, I've been,
like, in an alliance with them.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> But just something, something
is really striking me weird
right now that, that I didn't
feel before.
And, um, they told me that if
you give Kenny the, uh, the
necklace, then he's going to...
they're going to blindside you.
That's the plan.
And, uh, see, I wouldn't know
that unless they told me that.
So... I think that you shouldn't
do everything that they say.
I think we need to take them
out.
I mean, I just wanted to talk
to you about it.
You don't have to make any
decisions.
You can vote for whoever you
want.
>> So where's Susie stand in
all this?
>> I-I really don't know what
Susie's doing.
I'm sure she's going to vote
for whoever Matty votes for.
And I think we should vote for
Crystal.
>> Sugar said to me that it was
a blindside coming, which is an
interesting thing because she
hasn't done anything to show me
I can trust her.
She has not done anything that
shows me I can't trust her.
So I want to believe, but she's,
um, she-she's playing the game.
>> I appreciate that.
Um...
>> I mean, it's-it's a big
decision for you, and I
understand that.
But I just want you to look out
for yourself.
I will not vote for you.
I know you're the biggest
threat, but I don't care.
I just think the good guys
should win in the end.
>> What are we going to do if
he doesn't give me the idol?
>> I'm going home, obviously.
>> Hmm?
>> I think he might do it.
>> Why? What happened?
>> I just talked to him for a
little bit, and I was like...
I hate lying to Bob because I
really, really like Bob.
But it is a game.
I just told him that Kenny's
next.
I think. We'll see.
>> Bob thinks that I'm on the
outskirts with him, and, um,
I've made him think that.
Hopefully, he will give me that
immunity necklace, and Bob goes
home tonight.
But if not, then Matty will be
going home instead.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm definitely playing my
idol at Tribal because it's my
last day to do it.
Maybe I should give it to Matty
and save Matty, but I don't
want anybody to blindside me.
Just as long as Matty listens
to me, and Bob knows to trust
me, everything's going to be
fine.
>> PROBST: Now bring in
the members of our jury.
Marcus, Charlie, Randy...
and Corinne, voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
So, Bob, let's start with you.
Four challenges in a row.
There's no hiding; you're a
legitimate threat in this game.
>> You hit the nail right on
the head.
It's a huge target on my back.
And if I don't win, I could be
joining the jury.
>> PROBST: Kenny, you start
seeing a guy like Bob bring it
on strong, he could win his way
to the final Tribal Council.
>> Yeah, he amazes me, you
know, for being as old as he is.
He's strong.
He's smart.
He's agile.
He's, he's Bob.
>> PROBST: Matty, when you see
Bob win challenge after
challenge, what starts going
through your head?
>> You know, if anybody is
going to dominate at this game,
I'm really happy that it's this
man next to me, Bob, because
it's a lot better him having
that necklace around his neck
than somebody of a little less
caliber.
>> PROBST: Susie, a lot going
on these last few days.
Hard to be away on Exile?
>> Yeah, when you're away like
that and you come back into the
game, it's like, wow.
You just miss bits and pieces.
And then I have to rely on my
own gut instincts, so...
Even now, I'm still not certain.
>> PROBST: Kenny, with only six
people left, why do you think
Bob chose you as one of the
people to go on the gorilla
reward?
>> Um, basically, at the last
Tribal Council, uh, I-I flopped.
I believed in Bob, and once I
got back to camp, everybody
noticed that I was the one who
flopped.
And I was very frustrated, and I
asked him, "Why did you lie to
me, Bob?"
And Bob promised me something.
He-he told me that he would try
his best to win the next
immunity challenge, and he would
give me the immunity necklace if
he did win it.
>> PROBST: Bob, is that true?
>> That's-that's what I told
him.
Uh, we have since then sort of
renegotiated things.
Uh, I told him that if I feel
that he is going to go home
tonight, that I'd give him
the necklace.
And after we discuss all this,
I'll make that decision.
>> PROBST: And, Kenny, you're
making the case tonight that
you feel you're in danger.
>> I was at such a great
position, and now I'm on the
outcast.
You know, I turned on my
alliance.
Bob has the necklace, and where
am I?
>> PROBST: Crystal, got to make
you feel a little good that
Bob, who clearly has some power
in this game, picked you as one
of the people to go on a big
reward.
>> Um, I feel that he chose me
because I haven't been on a
reward in the 36 days that
we've been here.
And I feel honored to at least
get some kind of culture from
being here in Africa.
>> PROBST: Matty, do you think
that's all it was... Bob just
wanted somebody to have a
cultural experience, nothing to
do with an opportunity to bond
with two people who could help
you get further in the game?
>> I believe Bob knows that
Kenny and Crystal are the
tightest alliance since day one
in this game, and they have
honestly dominated this game.
>> PROBST: Kenny, you're
shaking your head.
>> I think that everybody
thinks that me and Crystal are
very tight, but I jumped from
my really good position in the
five alliance that I had, and I
feel like I could be the next
to go.
>> PROBST: So, based on what
you're saying then, how much
more important is the deal you
may or may not have made with
Bob tonight?
>> It makes the deal even more
important to me because I've
had a feeling all day that it
might be me.
>> PROBST: Matty, how you
feeling tonight?
>> Uh, very vulnerable.
And, uh, I don't have that
necklace on me, so that puts me
on the chopping block next.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about the
hidden immunity idol.
I just want to remind everybody
that tonight is the last night
you can play...
>> The hidden immunity idol?
(Sugar laughs)
>> PROBST: You're claiming
that's a hidden immunity idol?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: I guess if you play
it, we'll find out that if it
is.
Wouldn't be the first time
somebody's played an idol that
wasn't the idol.
(Sugar laughs)
>> I didn't make that one.
(Bob chuckles)
>> PROBST: Bob, it's time to
vote.
You have the individual
immunity necklace.
You can keep it for yourself.
You can give it to somebody
else, including Kenny, if you
want to.
It is up to you.
>> I told Kenny if I thought he
was going home tonight, I would
give it to him.
And...
I'm going to keep it because
I don't think he's going home
tonight.
>> PROBST: All right, so, you
cannot vote for Bob.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Crystal, you're up.
>> You were once part of my
alliance.
You wrote my name down one
time, and it's time for me to
pay you back.
>> Crystal, I've been waiting
for this day for a long time,
and I'm very happy that it's
finally arrived.
>> Dude, you don't know how to
talk or deal with people.
So, good luck with that jury
over there.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
>> PROBST: Thank you.
The rules of Survivor state that
if somebody plays a hidden
immunity idol, then any votes
cast against that person will
not count.
The person with the next
highest number of votes will be
voted out.
This is indeed the hidden
immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Matty will
not count.
I'll now read the votes.
First vote: Matty.
Does not count.
Matty.
Next vote: Crystal.
One vote for Crystal.
Crystal.
Two votes Crystal.
13th person voted out and the
fifth member of our jury:
Crystal.
That's three votes.
That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Crystal, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> PROBST: Well, we are down to
five.
The million dollars is within
sight.
The question is, which one of
the five of you will win it.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: What else can happen
in a season filled with
blindsides, fake idols...
>> That would fool me.
>> PROBST: ...switches...
Drop your buffs.
>> What?!
>> PROBST: ...and more
surprises than ever before.
>> New tribes.
>> PROBST: Find out in a special
two-hour season finale, where
one of these five people will
become the sole Survivor.
>> Wow.
I did not know that Sugar
turned on me.
I don't know what for.
It kind of hurts with three
days left in the game, but when
I yelled at Matty, I don't think
it helped.
It's been a great run, 36 days.
Tried to play a fair game, and
hopefully I made my friends and
family proud.