>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
On day 22, Marcus, the leader
of the Kota alliance, was so
confident, he was able to throw
away a hidden immunity idol.
>> These people are so stupid.
I got ten people to throw
an immunity idol into the ocean.
>> That is a very prized
possession there this game,
and somebody is really going
to wish they had that in a few
days.
>> PROBST: But the days of Kota
dominance were coming to an end.
By using brilliant strategy,
a rival alliance led by Kenny...
>> Behind the scenes, I'm really
calling the shots.
>> PROBST: ...has systematically
dismantled their foes.
They even tricked Randy into
playing a fake idol.
This is not a hidden immunity
idol.
(Sugar laughing)
Sending him home and humiliating
him at the same time.
>> It wasn't just "ha, ha, ha."
It was on and on and on.
(Sugar laughing)
And I was, to say the least,
irritated.
>> PROBST: Can Bob and Corinne,
the two remaining Kota, come up
with a brilliant strategy of
their own to stay in the game?
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
>> That was crazy.
>> Yeah.
>> The best Tribal so far, for
sure.
>> I think it was.
>> Bob, was that was your idea
to give Randy that fake idol?
>> Don't laugh like that.
You know, that pisses me off,
that part of sticking it in his
face.
I didn't mind doing the thing,
but then to just belittle him
as he was going out pisses me
off.
>> I'm sorry, Bob.
>> I'm over it now, but don't
ever do that again.
>> I really am sorry.
I know you feel bad.
I'm sorry.
I don't feel one iota, a bit
sorry for Randy because he dug
his own grave, and it's
hilarious that somebody gave
him a fake idol and he played
it.
>> For all the lessons you got
to teach me, right, about not
talking-- not belittling people.
>> Corinne, you talk about
people all the time behind their
back, and then to their face,
you act like a really sweet,
little girl with a little bow
on your head.
Come on.
>> I'm not acting like a sweet
girl.
If I told everybody to their
face what I said behind their
back, I wouldn't be playing
a very good game, would I?
>> Well, you shouldn't be
talking about people behind
their back that you don't even
know.
>> Why not? It's Survivor.
You don't come here to make
friends.
You come here to play the game.
You said it yourself.
>> Right, exactly.
You hit the nail on the head,
Corinne.
We're here to play the game,
and we're playing the game.
>> I am...
In general, I'm a nice person
to people I like.
I am now in a camp of mutants,
none of whom I like, so it's
very difficult for me to pretend
to be nice to them.
That's not something I'm used
to, and that's done.
(chewing loudly)
(elephant trumpets)
>> Oh!
>> Careful of them, careful.
>> Oh...
>> And look at this guy.
Look at this guy.
>> Oh, my...
Look how...
Ah, he's heavy.
I would never have imagined me
being out here and catching
fish.
I'm not an outdoorsy types
of person.
I'm just a gamer at home,
but out here, I'm my own man.
So I am very proud of myself,
because guys like me would
never ever be out here in
a situation like this, but only
in the game of Survivor.
>> We're going to eat today,
you people!
>> That is huge, Bob.
>> That's the biggest fish I
think I've ever seen anybody
catch.
>> That thing is huge.
Wow, that looks like a mini
shark.
>> This is crazy.
I've been able to catch tilapia,
turtle and big catfishes.
>> Yeah!
>> This is weird.
>> And little catfishes.
>> And little baby ones
and crawfish.
It's kind of weird.
>> There you go. That way.
>> Yeah.
>> Bob doesn't look out for
himself.
He doesn't know how to play this
game at all.
He's just here to build things,
and that's stupid, you know?
You know, he's taught me a lot
out here, but as far as playing
the game, he's not very good
at it.
>> Good job, Bob.
>> So I don't mind getting rid
of Bob.
And I feel like I need to pull
the power into my own hands and
take charge.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
♪ ♪
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will divide into
two teams of three.
On my go, you will race out
into the swamp, where you will
find two stations of
sprocket-shaped puzzle pieces.
Once you've collected all seven
pieces, you must then arrange
the pieces so they work
together allowing to you raise
the flag.
The first team of three to raise
their flag moves on to the final
round, where you will square off
against each other to solve
a slide puzzle.
The first person to solve
the slide puzzle wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: 31 days is a long
time to be without love.
I wish I could tell you
your loved ones were here,
coming around the corner.
They're not.
But that doesn't mean you can't
have a little love right now.
I have a Samsung Instinct
by Sprint.
Loaded onto this phone are video
messages from your loved ones
at home.
I'm going to give you a little
taste of that love right now.
Here's Andre and Destiny.
>> Hi, Crystal, this is Dre,
your big, old boo.
Just want you to know that
everything is going well here
on the home front.
>> Hi, Mommy, this is Destiny.
I love you. Be safe.
>> Oh, thank you.
I needed that.
>> PROBST: All right, Kenny, you
ready for a little love?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Kenny, here's your
sister, Jenny.
>> Hey, Ken, it's Jenny.
Uh, I love you so much.
I miss you.
Do your best, and never give up.
(sniffling)
>> I can't believe I'm crying.
>> PROBST: Why?
>> I miss her.
I miss her.
I miss family.
I mean, it's been rough.
>> PROBST: You guys can crowd
around, too, if you want to see
each other's.
>> Oh, you guys get to see
my baby, I hope.
>> PROBST: All right, Susie.
Here's your husband.
>> Hey, hon, we miss you
something terrible.
>> We miss you a lot.
>> Look at my baby.
>> Oh, it's terrible how bad it
is around here without you being
here.
The house is way too quiet.
>> Aw...
>> PROBST: Your man and your
son, your two men.
>> That's my baby.
That's my man!
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, Corinne.
>> Hi, Corinne.
We miss you.
Hey, sis.
Uh, hope you're doing good out
there.
Kind of miss you over here.
I've got no one to talk to
when I've got something crazy
to tell someone.
>> PROBST: You got the whole
family and the brother.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: All right, Bob.
Here's Peggy.
>> Hi, Bob.
How're you doing?
I hope that you're doing really
well.
What I mostly hope is that
you're having the adventure
of your lifetime.
>> She's pretty.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> PROBST: Now, that's support.
All she said was, "I just hope
you're having the adventure
of a lifetime."
>> Yeah.
She's behind me a hundred
percent.
I'm the luckiest man in the
world.
>> PROBST: Aw.
Matty, you look anxious.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: You want to go next?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right.
Who do you want to hear from?
>> Jamie.
>> PROBST: All right.
>> Hi, baby.
How are you doing?
We're happy as can be.
Yet, we do miss our other
partner, our family member,
Matty.
And don't ever forget that we
love you.
And we'll be here when you
return.
I love you so much.
(overlapping chatter)
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: Matty!
>> Yup.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Last, but certainly
not least, Sugar.
Here's your sister, Rena.
>> Hey, Jessica, I hope you're
enjoying yourself.
You have us supporting you all
the way, but especially Dad,
who's smiling down at you from
above.
And remember that we love you
so much.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Pretty nice message.
>> It's really nice to see her
and hear that from her.
>> PROBST: All right, guys.
Thanks for sharing those
with me.
All right, so, the winner of
today's challenge will enjoy
their entire loved one message--
there is more-- on the Sprint
phone, while enjoying a nice
little afternoon of pizza, beer,
brownies...
You'll fill up your belly and
you will fill up your heart.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: One more thing,
because today is all about
love, nobody is going to Exile
Island.
All right, we're going to draw
for teams.
Take a stone.
Please don't look.
Come on, now, keep it covered.
All right, everybody, palms out
and reveal.
If you have a yellow or red,
you're a captain.
Take a spot over here.
Crystal and Susie.
All right, we're going to rock,
paper, scissors-- see who goes
first.
>> One, two, three.
>> Scissors.
>> PROBST: Scissors cuts paper.
Susie, you choose first.
Who do you want on your team?
>> Matty.
>> PROBST: Crystal, who do you
want?
Sugar.
>> PROBST: Matty's choice.
>> Kenny.
>> PROBST: Kenny.
Sugar, who do you want?
>> Bob.
>> PROBST: Bob.
We have our two teams.
It is Sugar, Crystal, and Bob,
taking on Kenny, Matty, and
Susie.
Corinne, not chosen.
Corinne will not have any shot
of winning this reward.
>> When they started to pick,
and Crystal immediately picked
Sugar, I realized right away
they're all about, you know,
sticking together, sticking
together, and it sucks.
You know, I don't want to go
home.
And I don't know, you know, what
to do to save myself.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Out into the muddy swamp.
Crystal, Sugar, Bob, all take
a hard fall right off the bat.
Crystal dragging Sugar.
>> Stay on the mark.
>> PROBST: Crystal not slowing
down for anybody.
Gonna have to work together or
this is going to be really
frustrating.
Crystal, Sugar, Bob, first with
their pieces.
Matty, Susie, and Kenny right
behind.
Sugar goes down again.
That swamp is thick with mud.
Hard to move.
Matty, Susie and Kenny now
making up a lot of ground.
Crystal now stuck.
Matty, Kenny, Susie back with
their first three pieces.
>> Good job, girl, good job.
>> Okay...
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Crystal, Sugar, Bob,
back with their first three
pieces.
How much do you want that love?
Pizza, beer, brownies.
Long video message from home.
Kenny, Susie and Matty have
a good stride going.
Working well together.
>> Over here, baby.
>> PROBST: Everybody exhausted.
Matty, Susie, Kenny have their
last four sprocket pieces,
heading back.
>> Matty, Matty!
>> I can't!
>> Go...
>> I have no hands.
>> I know, I know, Matty, but...
>> PROBST: Bob, Crystal, Sugar
have their final four sprocket
pieces.
They're heading back.
Kenny, Susie, Matty, extending
their lead.
Bob, Sugar, Crystal playing it
very safe.
>> This is it! This is it!
This is it!
>> PROBST: Matty, Kenny, Susie
back with their final four
sprocket pieces.
Start working the puzzle.
Huge time advantage for Matty,
Kenny, and Susie.
>> Come on, Crystal.
>> PROBST: Bob, Sugar and
Crystal are back.
Start working on it.
All the pieces should interlock,
so that when you turn them,
they will raise the flag.
(indistinct chatter)
Bob, the physics teacher,
leading his team.
Kenny, the gamer, leading his
team.
>> Whoa, wrong one.
Where's the small one?
>> Right behind you.
>> Spin.
>> PROBST: Bob, Sugar, and
Crystal making a lot of
progress.
Getting very close with the
yellow team.
>> Pull it!
>> PROBST: Bob thinks they have
it.
And they do.
Sugar, Crystal, Bob moving on
to the final round.
>> Nice comeback, guys.
>> Sorry, guys.
>> PROBST: First to solve this
slide puzzle wins reward.
Survivors ready?
Go.
In front of you is what you are
trying to duplicate.
Bob thinks he has it.
And very quickly, Bob wins
reward!
(applause)
>> Wow, go, Bob!
>> Yeah, bob!
>> PROBST: That was fast.
Bob, come on over.
Congratulations.
Pizza, beer, brownies, loved one
from home on the Sprint phone.
This is for you.
>> Thanks, I appreciate it.
>> PROBST: All right, for the
rest of you, sorry, I got
nothing for you.
Head back to camp.
>> I really wanted to win
that reward.
I just wanted to see the whole
message that my sister had for
me, but Bob won.
And we think he's a threat.
So if he doesn't win immunity,
then he's next to go.
>> Hi, Bob. How're you doing?
You know, I miss you an awful
lot.
I know you're going to do well,
and... oh, wait a second.
There's something that I wanted
to show you. Hang on.
>> Oh, my God!
(laughter)
>> Can you believe this?
Look what we have!
>> I know.
>> You got a little treat.
Is this how you been eating?
>> Oh, yes.
Wait, I'll go get some termites.
>> Oh... no.
>> Oh, yeah, we've been eating
termite and turtle soup.
>> The moment I saw Bob, I
couldn't believe what he looked
like.
I was just so excited 'cause he
smelled like a campfire.
He smelled so good and he had
that full beard.
Your shirt!
(laughter)
>> My yellow shirt!
>> Oh, Bob!
He looks dirty, but I can tell
he's very happy.
You look really good.
>> Peggy's here.
I was completely convinced,
as was everybody else, that the
loved ones sent a video.
Cheers!
We're in Africa!
(laughter)
>> Y'all was like, "Crystal, are
you okay?"
>> Then you were, like...
You couldn't even get the
strength up to get back on the
thing.
You just stood there.
(laughter)
(Bob whistles)
>> Oh! Oh, my God, it's Peggy!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Are you kidding?!
>> She's coming!
>> This is where you are.
>> This is home.
>> Oh.
(indistinct chatter)
>> It's nice to meet you.
>> Hi.
>> So wait, you got to see our
loved ones?
>> It's really nice to meet you.
>> Did you see my sister?
>> Did you see my husband?
>> Hi, Matt.
Nice to see you.
>> Nice to see you, Peggy.
>> Who's that?
>> Kenny.
Kenny, how nice to meet you.
Matthew.
>> Watch, this is really cool.
Watch this.
(Bob whistles)
>> Oh, my God!
>> No, my... oh, no, please.
>> Oh, my... God.
(sobbing)
>> Oh, my God.
(laughing and crying)
>> I was so happy to see Andre.
I mean, "happy" is just not
good enough to explain.
I haven't seen him in so long.
And it was just so good to hold
him.
>> We totally didn't expect to
see you guys.
I mean, we were talking about
it.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Seeing my brother, and seeing
somebody who loves me and who
knows me and who gets my sense
of humor, and who knows how mean
I am and loves it, was such a
cool-- like, just... I was
overcome with emotion.
>> "Nobag."
>> I have a secret two alliance.
It's Sugar and Crystal, the big
one.
>> Okay.
>> And they trust me a hundred
percent because I saved both
their asses.
I saved both their asses.
>> Okay.
>> And right now, everybody
trusts me.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> But I will blindside Matty.
I took out, Jenny, I took out
five powerhouses, big guys.
Everybody loves me.
If I make the final three, I
will win this game.
>> Well, I'll tell you one
thing: Dad would be so proud of
you.
>> Yeah.
I did Survivor because I thought
it might help me get a little
bit of closure from my dad's
passing.
So my sister brought some of my
dad's ashes.
>> Do you want to say a prayer?
>> Yeah.
Thanks, Dad, for everything
you've done for me, and I know
that you're the one...
You're the reason that I'm here.
And that you're with me every
day that I've been here,
especially when we were on
Exile.
And thank you for this awesome
opportunity.
And thanks for being here with
me and keeping me strong, and
letting me see Rena and having
all this incredible stuff
happen.
>> Have fun in Africa, Dad.
(laughs)
>> I didn't speak at his funeral
because I was a big mess.
So it felt good to say a few
words because I really needed
him here and I feel like he's...
Like, I already felt like he was
here, but I feel like, um, I
brought him to Africa and he got
to stay.
>> Where are we going?
>> Down here.
>> Okay.
>> I've always been kind of weak
and I've always wanted to avoid
the tough things in life, you
know?
Like settling down and being
an adult, you know?
And that's what I realized out
here.
I got to face up to my fears
and grow up.
And I don't want to let another
day pass and me not let Jamie
know how much she means to me
and how much I value her.
>> This is incredible.
I love this.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I love you, baby.
>> Hey...
(whispers): I love you.
I want to spend the rest of my
life with you.
>> I want to do the same, baby.
I want to do the same with you.
>> I want to share family with
you.
And I want to share kids.
And I want to share the future,
and I want to share the past,
and I want to share everything,
Jamie.
I really...
>> We will, baby, we will.
>> And I want us... I just want
to know right now.
I really want you to be my wife.
And I want... I want to marry
you and I want you to be my
wife.
And I made this for you.
Will you be my wife?
>> Yes, baby.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
>> I'm being serious.
I'm not joking around or joking.
I really love you.
Okay, let me put it on really
fast.
>> I love you.
>> Here, I made it for you.
>> You made this?
>> Yeah, should I get on my
knees?
Will you be my wife?
>> Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
>> I love you, Jamie.
(indistinct chatter)
>> The whole experience today,
it means everything to me.
Because I know that Todd's
really proud of me, so that
makes me feel really good.
>> The good things in life
aren't easy.
And they require a lot of work
and a lot of digging deep.
And if you keep digging, you
will find it.
I mean, it's endless.
You have so much ability
and gold in you.
And if you just dig for it,
you will find it.
>> Hey, two peeps.
Who wants to get tree mail?
>> I'll go.
>> Corinne, go get tree mail.
>> I'll go with Corinne.
>> Yeah, go.
>> All right.
>> Get going.
>> You guys want to go.
Have fun.
>> Okay, we'll be right back.
>> Bye.
>> You know, there is a
possibility, very slight, that
they might get rid of Matty
if he doesn't win immunity.
>> Here's what I'm thinking...
>> You guys, don't you think
it's weird that there's a tribe
of people are living together
and a couple that of them know
they're going?
It's so weird.
>> They're outside, outskirts.
>> As for now, our five are
sticking together because we
have a better chance that way.
Hopefully, nobody's going
to flip.
>> He's good at everything.
You're the only person that
stands a chance against Bob in
a physical challenge, really.
>> Yeah.
>> That's true, Matty.
>> The plan is to vote out Bob
and then Corinne because Bob is
way bigger of a threat.
>> Remember when we threw the
idol into the ocean?
>> Yes.
>> And they never went and
checked the bottle.
But Marcus threw it in.
Did you know that he had the
idol in his pocket when he came
back and hid it around camp?
And showed me where it was.
And said, "It's hidden over
here."
>> No way.
He didn't have it when he went
to Tribal, so if I win immunity,
I can give that to you.
>> That's a legit idol?
>> No, but it sounded pretty
good, didn't it?
>> Oh. Yeah, it did sound good.
>> I'm going to put it together,
and I'm going to imply that I've
got the idol we were supposed
to have thrown in the ocean.
>> Wow.
>> I am going to make my second
very good fake idol of the game.
And the plan with the idol is,
I'm going to tell somebody on
the other side that I've got the
the original idol that was
supposed to have gone into the
ocean, so they've got to be
careful how they vote.
>> Good for you, Bob.
Good plan.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> You got it.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first--
Kenny, give it up.
(laughs)
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, I'm
going to ask you questions
about Gabon.
Each time you answer correctly,
you earn a ball.
You're then going to take turns
throwing your balls toward
a target divided by zones.
The person who lands their ball
in a zone closest to the center
wins immunity, guaranteed a
one-in-six shot at winning this
game.
Losers go to Tribal Council
where somebody will be voted
out.
Anything not clear?
Let's get started.
All right, here we go.
First question, true or false:
gorillas were actually first
discovered here in Gabon?
All right, everybody, reveal.
Correct answer is...
true.
Sugar got it right.
Corinne got it right.
Gorillas were discovered here
in 1847.
Sugar gets a ball.
Corinne gets a ball.
Next question: a male elephant
is called a bull.
A female elephant is called:
"A," a mare; "B," a doe;
or, "C," a cow.
Everybody reveal.
Correct answer is "C," the cow.
Sugar got it right.
Susie got it right.
Corinne got it right.
And Bob got it right.
Next question.
It is a fact that the Gabonese
viper is a poisonous snake.
True or false: it is considered
virtually harmless to humans.
Everybody reveal.
Susie and Corinne say it is
true that it is virtually
harmless to humans.
A poisonous snake, Susie and
Corinne, is deadly to humans.
The answer is false.
Yes, it was a trick question.
Good news is, everybody's
on the board.
Everybody's going to get
at least one shot at the target.
Sugar currently in front with
three shots.
Last question, true or false:
the elephant's trunk has three
purposes: it serves as its
nose, its arm, and its mouth.
Everybody reveal.
Crystal says true.
Susie says true.
The trunk is the nose and the
arm.
It is not the mouth.
Kenny got it right.
Matty got it right.
Sugar got it right.
Corinne got it right and Bob
got it right.
All right, well, we know what
you know about Gabon.
Let's see how it plays out.
Head over here.
Kenny, you're first up.
>> Good luck, Kenny.
>> Let's do this.
>> PROBST: Kenny has two balls.
Using your first one.
No hesitation.
>> What?! Oh!
>> PROBST: Nice shot, sixth
zone from the center.
Matty, you're trying to get as
close as you can to that center
zone.
That looks good.
Fourth zone from the center.
Matty is now the mark to beat.
Sugar.
Ooh, soft launch, going to look
for some roll.
She gets it.
Not close enough.
Matty, still the mark to beat.
Susie, you get one shot.
Don't be short, woman.
Come strong.
Good launch.
Not going to be good enough.
No shot at winning immunity.
Corinne.
Ooh, good-looking toss.
Nobody.
No, fifth zone from the middle.
Matty's still the mark to beat.
Bob going to take his first
shot.
>> It's all physics.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Good follow-through.
Look at that.
Bob, with his first toss,
is now the mark to beat.
>> Good job, Bob.
>> Nice job.
>> PROBST: Crystal got one
question right and gets only one
shot.
Crystal with no backspin.
Gets a good roll.
Not good enough.
Crystal's now out of the
challenge.
Kenny.
Kenny launches it.
Oh, it was in, and then out.
>> Oh, Kenny!
>> PROBST: Kenny is out of this
challenge now.
Matty with his last shot at
this.
>> No, Matt.
>> PROBST: Nope, Matty falls
short.
Matty is now out of this
challenge.
No shot at winning.
Sugar up next.
Nice, little soft touch.
Oh, just misses.
Not close enough.
Corinne is up.
Big immunity on the line.
Good toss.
Too far out.
Bob's up.
He is already the mark to beat.
He can afford to be a little
risky now.
It's going to be short.
Will it roll?
It does.
Bob improves his mark.
He is now one zone from the
center.
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: Going to be very
tough to beat Bob.
Sugar.
Sugar going for the roll, and
she won't get it.
Bob, still the mark to beat.
Corinne, your last shot at
immunity.
Goes very high.
Will she get a good kick?
She does.
Is it going to be enough? No.
(Corinne groans)
Corinne has no shot at immunity.
Bob, with your last ball.
Bob doesn't improve his lie.
Bob is still the mark to beat,
though.
One last shot.
Sugar, this is it.
You need to get in either the
center zone or the first zone
outside of the center.
Anything else doesn't matter.
Sugar launches it.
And a good roll.
It's in and out of the center.
Bob wins immunity!
>> Good job, Bob.
>> Handshake?
>> PROBST: Bob, come on over.
(applause)
Nice job.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> PROBST: Bob is safe
at tonight's Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out of this
game.
One-in-six shot at winning it
all.
For the rest of you, Tribal
Council tonight, where one of
you will be voted out of this
game.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I'll see you at Tribal.
>> Winning today's immunity
challenge saved me.
I'm going to get the fake idol
built.
There are five Fang members
here, and I'm going to suggest
that two of them go in with
Corinne and I.
If all goes as planned, perfect
time to blindside Matty.
>> Well done, Bob.
>> Yeah, very good.
I felt like such a big dunce.
>> Obviously, Bob and I know
that our numbers are up, so
we've got this whole back story
about why we have the idol that
was supposedly launched into
the ocean at the Fake Out Feast.
But what we needed to have this
work correctly was at least one
of us to get the immunity idol,
which is exactly what happened.
The story is this: Marcus got
the idol.
You were the only person that
knew about it.
I've never known about it.
>> Right.
If you hadn't gotten immunity
tonight, you would have used it
for yourself.
But you got immunity, and the
only way to keep yourself in
this game is to give it to me
so that I'm still in the game,
and to take out the strongest
player, being Matty.
If they think I'm going to play
the idol, they're not going
to want to vote me.
>> You are a conniving son
of a gun.
>> So are you.
>> Thank you very much.
>> I hope this works.
It's such a long shot, but it's
all we got.
Let's do it.
I think I'm very smart, and I
think Bob is very crafty.
And we put those two forces
together.
This was the best we could do.
It would be so awesome if this
worked.
>> The only thing, I think,
Corinne's trying to make Bob
give her the immunity necklace.
>> Probably.
>> If he gives it to her, it's
still before for the vote.
So, we just... Bob's got to go.
>> Yeah, all we know is this
five is tight and we're staying
strong.
And Corinne's gone.
No one's flipping.
No, we're good.
I don't know why everybody's
worried.
>> 'Cause this game makes you
worry, man.
>> Bob, uh, won the immunity
challenge today.
So, uh, today we need to vote
out Corinne.
But it's dangerous.
We're getting down to the final
six with Bob still in it, and
Bob's a major threat when it
comes down to it, so... it's
nerve-wracking, man.
>> You really can't say
anything.
>> I promise. I swear.
>> So remember when they threw
the idol out into the ocean?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Well, Marcus ripped the
string, but had the rest of the
idol in his pocket.
Never put it in the ocean.
He brought it back to camp and
hid it with Bob.
But since he won immunity
today, he's like, "Listen, if we
use it now, you know, it will
help."
>> Who are you guys going
to take out?
>> We're taking out Matty, and
that's it.
So he may end up going home,
but I know I'm not.
>> I think right now, your
and Bob's best chance is to
take out Matty.
>> Let me see if I can get Bob.
>> Yeah, I think you, me and Bob
should talk.
>> Well, he doesn't know I told
you yet.
Let me, uh, soften the blow.
Give me a second, Kenny.
>> This has definitely changed
the game, and I think the best
shot is to blindside Matty
right now.
I think I might have to jump
alliances now.
Oh, my God.
>> Yeah.
>> So we're trying to figure out
the best way to strategize.
I don't know.
>> I think the best option is...
>> Yeah, tell us, 'cause you're
just as smart as we are,
and we need your input.
>> I know Matty's not that
smart.
>> So I'm wondering...
>> Marcus took it off...
>> Do you think maybe the better
person 'cause she's smarter
than the rest of them, is
Crystal?
Do you think Crystal would
separate from the others?
>> I think Crystal would
probably join us.
>> So maybe...
>> And if we get Crystal in,
we'll go to the final four.
>> Yup.
>> And we'll figure it out
from there.
>> Yeah.
We come up with a ridiculously
harebrained scheme that
shouldn't work at all, and it
might actually work, which is
so mind-blowing.
It just shows you the level of,
like, incompetence we're playing
with.
>> What we're going to do is
ask Crystal if she'd like to be
on our alliance.
And we're giving her the chance
to join with us.
I just collected these pieces.
I'm worse than a raven.
I save everything.
I don't know about you, but
that would fool me.
(chittering)
>> How close were you to Marcus
when he threw it in?
>> We were far.
>> Yeah.
You saw the idol that was
on the bottle, right?
>> Yeah.
>> It had a face on it.
It was...
>> Right.
>> That's the idol.
>> Final four: you, me, Kenny,
and Corinne.
We don't want to use this
tonight.
Would you be interested in
taking out Matty tonight?
Go on board with us.
>> I'm on board.
>> Operation Fake Idol II is
working like a charm.
And the interesting thing is
we're not even going to have
to use the idol.
>> Bob said "Matty."
>> We're taking out Matty?
Even better for us.
>> Look, we have to flush out
their idol.
>> Bob shook my hand and gave
me a kiss on the cheek.
>> What?
>> So that's a big deal for him.
>> Okay, look, you have to vote
for Corinne.
>> Okay.
>> You understand that.
>> Yes.
>> Everybody's voting for
Corinne.
>> Yes.
>> Okay, I'm going to vote for
Matty.
>> That'll be three for Matty.
>> Three for Matty.
>> And four for Corinne.
>> Yeah, I'll make sure he plays
the idol, so the idol's gone,
Matty's gone-- boom!
This is the best plan.
I know for a fact that Crystal
is going to vote for Corinne.
And Corinne is going to play her
idol, a win-win situation for
me because the idol's flushed
out and Matty's going to be
going home.
So if this plan works out, oh,
I'll be the biggest strategist
in Survivor history.
>> But it's going to be a little
tense there tonight.
>> We'll have numbers out there
tonight anyways.
I think it's a good plan.
>> Yeah.
>> I think it's the best...
>> I think the four of us...
It's going to be my first flop
in the game, but hopefully, it's
a good choice.
>> Every fiber of me wants
to trust Kenny.
If the idol is real, then
Matty's gone.
But if they got a fake idol,
Corinne goes home, and I've
definitely been weighing who's
better to take out.
My heart tells me to take Matty
out.
Corinne is not the threat to me
in no way, shape or form.
This is, like, my only chance
to get him out, and it's been
wracking my brain.
The mental part of this game is
kicking my ass.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Marcus, Charlie, and Randy,
voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
Susie, can you still feel
old Tribal lines, or is now
this now "How do I win this
game?"
>> The alliances that you make
have to get you to a certain
point, and when people start
getting paranoid, it's a domino
effect.
So you do have to think ahead.
>> PROBST: Bob, does this make
sense, this paranoia?
Is that inevitable?
>> This is the first time I
haven't been paranoid.
I get to realize what it feels
like to have this on.
But I'll be paranoid next time
I come in here.
>> PROBST: Corinne, can
paranoia be an advantage?
>> I suppose it can.
You know, obviously, Bob and I
are kind of on the outside, and
they're a tight group of five.
If paranoia sets in, maybe
there is a possibility to try
and, you know, break it up.
>> PROBST: Sugar, what's the
worst part about paranoia as it
relates to your game?
>> People freaking out and
believing lies and flipping.
I mean, you just have to, like,
keep everybody in check and
make sure nobody is being
gullible and getting duped.
>> PROBST: Crystal, at a certain
point, does it become crazy
to trust?
>> With certain people, yes.
Certain people, no.
>> PROBST: And is the whole
trick of this game figuring out
when that time is?
>> That is the whole trick of
the game: knowing when to trust
and when to cut your ties.
>> PROBST: Kenny, is tonight's
vote any more important, less
important than any other vote?
>> I think it's very important
tonight.
Because you think that you can
trust somebody, and then you
don't.
Because after you see the
votes, you're going to be like,
"Whoa, who did this?
Who did that?"
So I would say tonight's vote is
very important, compared to any
other vote.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Bob, you have the individual
immunity necklace.
I assume you're going to keep
it for yourself tonight.
>> Very good assumption.
>> PROBST: Cannot vote for Bob.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Corinne, you're up.
>> Matty, this is clearly
a strategic move, and I'm sorry
to see you go, bro.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
> PROBST: If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
>> PROBST: Okay, once the votes
are read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Matty.
Corinne.
One vote Matty;
one vote Corinne.
Corinne.
Two votes Corinne;
one vote Matty.
Corinne.
That's three votes Corinne;
one vote Matty.
Matty.
Two votes Matty;
three votes Corinne.
Matty.
We're tied: three votes Corinne;
three votes Matty.
One vote left.
12th person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon and the fourth
member of our jury.
Corrine, you need to bring me
your torch.
Corinne, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Well, the big theme
of the night: paranoia.
The question is, how do you make
the paranoia work for you and
not against you?
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Okay.
Bob put himself in this
position.
He kind of messed with the
wrong guy.
>> Crystal and Kenny can take
out whoever they want.
Kenny acts like he's this weak,
little meager guy, and he spins
all these lies.
And Crystal is just a big bully.
I can't stand Sugar.
I'll never be able to stand
Sugar, and I plan to never
exchange another sentence with
that girl for the rest of my
life.
You know, I really just don't
like any of those people, other
than Bob and Kenny.
And I really, really, really
wish Kenny and Bob all the
best.
And I hope the rest of them