(elephant trumpeting)
(gorilla hooting)
>> JEFF PROBST: 36 days ago,
these 18 Americans arrived in
Gabon, Africa.
Welcome to Survivor: Gabon.
They were surrounded by endless
savannah and miles of jungle.
Their every move was shadowed
by dangerous wild animals.
They were as far away from
civilization as a person could
possibly be.
>> I see why they call it the
Garden of Eden.
>> PROBST: Red tribe, you are
Fang.
On the first day, the 18 were
split into two tribes.
Yellow, you are Kota.
From the beginning, the yellow
tribe looked as though they
were going to run away with the
game.
Kota wins immunity and fire!
Kota wins reward!
(cheering)
Kota wins immunity once again!
They won nine out of the first
11 challenges.
Kota, should be a fun afternoon.
Fang, I got nothing for you.
>> It's hard, you know, when
you see them walking away.
They have everything and we
have nothing.
>> PROBST: Kota was well-fed,
well-rested, and confident.
>> The best part about this is
they may be completely out of
the race.
>> A tribe switch put the two
Fang leaders on Kota, but just
when Kenny and Crystal appeared
to be doomed, they struck back,
overcoming their opponents'
strength with superior strategy.
The original Kota never knew
what hit them.
They fell like dominoes.
To add insult to injury, the
powerful twosome tricked their
worst enemy into playing a fake
hidden immunity idol.
This is not a hidden immunity
idol.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: When the fourth
consecutive Kota checked out,
it was a brand-new game.
Now there are only five players
left:
Susie, a teacher, hairdresser,
and mom.
>> Okay, I want to be honest
with you.
I was actually going to vote
you.
>> PROBST: A lot of her old
tribe mates thought she was a
bad strategist, but it was her
decision to flip that allowed
the original Fang to go on
their improbable run.
>> I might be riding coattails
here and there when I can, but
everybody's trying to do
everything they can to be that
sole Survivor.
>> PROBST: She's considered
weak at individual challenges,
yet she's already won a big one.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Susie wins immunity.
Matty, the personal trainer.
His physical strength was
supposed to carry him to the
end, but since the merge, he
hasn't won anything.
>> Matty is super-irritated.
You keep on winning challenges
and not him.
>> PROBST: He needs to win
immunity because he's still
considered to be a physical
threat.
>> If Fang takes the next
immunity challenge, they're
voting for me.
>> I'd say that's accurate.
>> PROBST: Sugar, the pin-up
model.
She's quick to tell everyone
she doesn't know how to play
the game.
>> Yeah, I'm an idiot.
Ding, ding, ding...
>> PROBST: She's been sent to
Exile Island five times in a
row.
>> I'm here to break records,
you know?
>> PROBST: So she's spent the
least least amount of time with
the others, but she's figured
out how to become the vital
swing vote in several
game-changing moments.
>> I think I'm the lady of the
hour.
>> PROBST: Bob, the 57-year-old
high school physics teacher, the
last of the old Kota tribe.
>> The next one to go is Bob,
so Bob should be worried.
>> PROBST: Bob has just won
reward!
He would have been voted out
a long time ago if he hadn't
gone on an amazing winning
streak.
Bob scores!
Bob wins immunity!
>> Four challenges in a row.
I'm 57 years old.
AARP is going to call up and ask
me to represent them.
>> PROBST: And Kenny, the
professional video game player.
If anyone can be called a
Survivor, it's him.
He's already survived 11 trips
to Tribal Council.
>> I have been calling the shots
since day one out here,
you know.
I am the mastermind.
>> PROBST: He'll say anything
to win and has no problem lying.
>> Kenny acts like he's this
weak, little meager guy, and he
spins all these lies.
>> Reporter: He's furious at
Bob because Bob promised to
give him the immunity necklace.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: And Kenny immediately
tried to stab Bob in the back.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Is that okay?
>> PROBST: But Sugar told Bob,
and the deal was off.
>> I was just ticked because I
realized he was going to whack
me.
>> PROBST: At the last Tribal
Council, Sugar, who had the
real hidden immunity idol for
the last 28 days, finally
decided to play it...
...not to protect herself,
but to save Matty.
Bob kept his immunity necklace
and a new alliance of four voted
out Kenny's closest
coconspirator, Crystal.
We're down to the final five.
Find out tonight who will
outwit, outplay, and outlast
all the others to become the
sole Survivor.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Well, I'd love to say that
was a perfectly executed play of
a hidden immunity idol.
>> Wow.
>> Congratulations, final five.
>> I know.
It's crazy.
I wasn't expecting that.
>> Handing over the immunity
necklace felt glorious.
I had to send Crystal home, and
I had that damn idol since the
first 24 hours at Exile, and I
didn't use it to the very end
and I used it to save Matty.
I like, literally, have never
felt so powerful in my life.
>> You know, in the woods
somewhere, here and there.
You know how it goes around
here, Kenny.
>> Why don't you get your own
idol?
>> I was out of the loop
tonight and I do feel a little
bit betrayed.
So, tonight at Tribal Council, I
called out Bob about the hidden
immunity necklace and he made up
a lie saying that if he thinks
that I'm going, that he'd give
it to me and that wasn't part of
the deal.
He's not a man of his word now.
You know, it's not like I don't
try to get my own idol.
I was pretty close today.
>> We'll see.
By announcing this whole deal
in front of everybody, I think
he was sort of trying to
embarrass me if I didn't stand
by my word.
For me, it's a little bit on the
annoying side.
That means all promises are off.
>> Congratulations again, Bob.
>> Oh, thanks.
>> You get a lot of respect from
everybody, man.
>> Yeah.
>> That means you're playing a
really, really good game, dude.
>> So, Kenny thinks we're in an
alliance from before, and she
still thinks that Matty's in an
alliance.
These guys don't know anything.
So I guess I'm just going to
keep playing like I'm with
Kenny.
He's going to keep playing
like he's with her, and we take
them all out.
Is that cool with you?
>> I would love to be in the
final three with Bob and Matty.
So that means the next two
people I would like to vote out
would be Sue and Kenny.
But when I knocked Crystal out
last night, it made Kenny maybe
not trust me so much.
So I'm going to make sure that
he feels safe as soon as
possible before he gets to Bob
or convinces Matty of something
and starts messing up my plan.
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
>> Cool!
>> Oh, my God.
I want this one.
Cool clothes or cloths or
something.
>> These are clothes.
>> Oh, my God.
I'm calling the blue one right
now.
>> Last night, I felt I got
blindsided and I felt a little
betrayal from Sugar.
But Sugar and I went on a walk
today and I feel comfortable
now.
I feel that Sugar has no
alliance to Susie, so I think
that Sugar really wants to take
me to the final three with her.
>> I mean, either way, Susie's
gone.
>> Susie's going home.
>> Yeah.
>> This is not another
blindside on me, right?
>> No!
>> Okay.
(laughing)
>> "A tribe of many colors,
red, yellow, white, black, and
blue.
Each of you, unique.
Like warriors when you're
through, an amazing chance
you've got,
an amazing trip you're on,
an amazing shot at a million
bucks if you conquer
amazing Gabon."
>> It's day 37, final five.
Feels great to be here.
I didn't think I was going to
make it this far, but we're
here.
We got a challenge coming up.
So, we have to kind of make our
own.
We got face paint, and some
material and beads and we have
to each uniquely dress ourselves
up as warriors, so I'm pumped
about that.
I am really proud of myself that
I've gotten this far, and I'm
still going to keep trying.
I wanted to get to the million
dollars.
That's my goal: got to win it.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Wow, I am impressed.
You guys look good.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
Matty, was it fun getting a
chance to create a new
character?
>> Yeah, it's fun.
I just hope my family and my
girlfriend still love me when I
get home after this.
I hope they don't think I lost
my mind.
>> PROBST: I think the person
who is going to take the most
grief is Bob.
Very Village People.
You guys ready to get to
today's immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Bob, once again, I will take it
back from you.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
dig under a wall, make your way
across a series of planks...
which will lead you into a maze
filled with Gabonese huts.
Inside three of the huts, you
will find bags of puzzle pieces.
Each time you find a bag, you
must make your way through the
maze, to the finish platform,
drop the bag, and then head out
to find another one.
Once you've collected all three
bags of puzzle pieces, you will
use those pieces to build a
replica of a Gabonese hut.
First person to build it
correctly wins immunity,
is guaranteed a one-in-four shot
at winning a million bucks.
All right, we'll get started.
This way.
Here we go, for immunity and a
guaranteed spot in the final
four.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First step is to dig a hole big
enough to get you underneath
that wall.
Once you think that hole is big
enough, pull your body through,
and you're on to the next phase.
Bob is stuck halfway.
Kenny trying to pull himself
through.
Susie going to give it a shot.
Susie is the first through, out
of nowhere.
Susie working her way on to the
planks.
Kenny's now through.
Bob is now through.
Matty's now through.
Sugar squeezing that booty
through.
(Sugar laughs)
Sugar's through now.
Everybody is now through.
This is an elevated maze.
Your goal is to figure your way
out along these planks to get
to the finish, which will lead
you into the maze of Gabonese
huts.
Bit of a guessing game.
A lot of forward thinking.
Matty falls off.
He's got to head all the way
back to the start.
Kenny almost falls off.
Nice save.
Susie thinks she has it.
Sugar following along.
Kenny following.
Susie can see the end.
Susie's through.
Sugar is through.
Kenny is through.
You have to untie a series of
knots to open a gate.
Sugar is first through.
Susie's through.
Matty can see the end.
Matty trying to get back in
this.
Matty's now across the planks.
Bob is now through his gate.
Kenny's now out on the maze.
Matty's out in the maze.
Everybody is now out in the
maze of Gabonese huts.
Everybody is looking for pieces.
There are 25 huts.
Only three of them have puzzle
pieces in them.
Once you find a bag, you got to
make your way all the way to
the finish.
Matty is the first one to the
top with his first bag of
puzzle pieces.
Kenny back with his first bag.
Susie right behind with her
first bag.
Bob and Sugar heading back with
their first bag of puzzle
pieces.
>> PROBST: Matty back with his
second bag of puzzle pieces.
Matty heads out looking for
that third and final bag.
Bob pulling himself up this
steep finish with that second
bag of puzzle pieces.
Sugar has her final bag of
puzzle pieces.
Bob has his final bag.
Sugar back with her final bag
of puzzle pieces.
Drop the bag, open them,
start working on the puzzle.
Bob is back with his final bag
of puzzle pieces.
Sugar and Bob now working on
the puzzle.
Matty trying to get in on it.
Kenny trying to get in on it.
Susie cannot find her last bag.
Win this challenge, you are
guaranteed a spot in the final
four.
Lose, you could be going home
tonight.
Bob making quick work of this
puzzle.
Kenny working to catch up.
Matty working to catch up.
Sugar looking very good.
Bob making a lot of progress.
He's close.
It's Sugar and Bob.
Bob wins immunity!
Five straight challenges!
>> Where's Susie?
>> PROBST: Bob, come on over.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: For the third
straight time, individual
immunity.
You are safe once again at
Tribal Council.
Kenny, Matty, Sugar, Susie,
tonight, after 37 hard-fought
days, one of you going home.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
I will see you at Tribal
Council.
>> My goal, obviously, was for
me to win, but that didn't
happen.
Bob, the wizard, fantastic Bob
won.
I don't know how you beat that
guy.
>> I set myself up so well in
this game right now that I
could just chill and relax all
day.
And, uh, I already confirmed it,
uh, today, uh, with Sugar during
our walk that, uh, if Bob wins,
then, uh, it's Susie that's
going to go first.
So I'm not worried.
>> Hey.
I think, uh, S-Sugar is going to
tell Susie that we're voting for
her.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> But we're going to wait
till the day's almost over, so
she doesn't start scrambling
around.
You realize I still haven't
written your name down, dude.
I'm not the type of person that
would blindside you.
If I was going to write your
name down, I'd tell you.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay?
>> I really want to go to the
end.
>> We're there.
Don't worry about it, bro.
>> Is Kenny working you?
Is he trying to...
What's he doing?
>> Not really.
>> Is that what we're doing,
is Kenny?
I don't know; you guys won't
tell me anything.
>> We don't... I'm not saying
anything 'cause I don't know,
Susie.
>> You still don't know?
>> I still don't know.
>> Usually, I know what's going
on because Matty will say
something to me.
But no one has talked to me,
so I-I feel a bit vulnerable.
Like, is it me?
I really don't know what I'm
doing now because nobody's
talking to me.
I hate that.
>> Do what you feel.
>> Yeah, but in this game, you
still have to try to get to the
top.
Still your goal is to try to
still be aligned and trust
people to get you to at least
the three, or at least the four.
>> Well, everybody's playing
for themselves tonight.
There's no way to trust anybody.
If you listen to yourself,
I think you'll be fine.
>> I had a little bit of a
heart-to-heart with Matty.
Anyway, and he's like, "Yeah,
just go with your gut."
You want to believe people are
telling you the truth, but, you
know, sometimes they're lying.
Sometimes they are telling
you the truth.
It's just when to know when to
believe it.
But I definitely feel nervous
that I could go tonight.
>> You and, you and me are
staying close to the end,
no matter what, no matter what,
you and I, you and I, no matter
what.
>> I know.
>> The final result in this
game should be you, me, and
Kenny.
>> For sure.
>> Me and Matty have an
understanding that Susie goes
next.
But Kenny is very smart, and,
um, he is dangerous to-to keep
around.
It seems like the further along
we are, the harder the
decisions get to as to who we
vote out.
I still don't know what I'm
going to do.
To get rid of Susie would be
great because I have no
allegiance with Susie, and I
don't trust her.
I would vote for Kenny because
he's a liar, and he could
manipulate Bob or Matty.
So I just have to think really
hard about what should be done.
No matter what I decide to do,
I think Bob and Matty will vote
with me.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Marcus, Charlie, Randy,
Corinne, and Crystal, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Bob, let's start with you.
Five consecutive wins.
Tied for a record in the history
of this game.
Do you feel the target on your
back getting larger and larger
with each win?
>> Yes.
That's why I keep working
harder and harder, trying to
make sure I have this necklace
on when I come here.
>> PROBST: Matty, as a
competitor, there has to be a
part of you that looks at Bob
with some admiration.
>> Yeah, Bob's money, man.
He's an expert at these
challenges.
And I don't know how he does it,
but there's not even a target on
his back 'cause we can't even
see him he's so far ahead of us,
you know.
The guy is just good.
>> PROBST: Kenny, it's got to
be a little frustrating.
>> The thing is about Bob and I,
we come from two different
backgrounds.
I mean, I'm a gamer.
I usually sit in front of TV
and play video games all day.
I don't do outdoorsy things.
While, you know, he's an
outdoorsy type of, type of guy.
He goes camping.
He does fishing.
And you know what?
That's how it is.
>> PROBST: Susie, you don't
want anybody to have any reason
to vote you out.
Are you a little concerned that
37 days in this game might give
people a reason to want to get
rid of you?
>> I want to feel comfortable,
but I'm not completely
comfortable all the time.
So I wait till somebody comes
to me and tells me something,
and it can work against me,
and it can work for me, also.
So...
>> PROBST: How does it work
against you?
>> Because I'm not
strategically making moves and
trying to talk to people and
asking questions and finding
out what's going on.
So that's what makes me feel a
little bit like an outsider.
>> PROBST: Kenny, do you feel,
coming into tonight's Tribal
that you've repaired any damage
you might have done over the
last 37 days?
>> I feel like I've repaired a
lot of damage.
I've made up with a lot of
people, and I feel like our
bonds are stronger that way.
>> PROBST: At the last Tribal
Council, there was some
discussion about a deal you had
made with Bob, that if he had
the necklace and felt you
needed it, he would give it to
you.
Did that come up today?
>> I really feel that Bob is
actually going to back down on
his deal because the deal was
that if he won the next
challenge, he'd give it to me.
And then he said, "Only if I
think you're going."
Apparently there was some small
print at the bottom of the
contract that you had to look
at through the magnifying glass
to see so I think that he's
pulling some loopholes around
the deal and trying to back out
of it somehow.
>> Well, what I didn't realize
was he went back to the tribe
and discussed with people that
when I gave him the necklace,
that they would then blindside
me.
I was trying to take care of
him and he was going to take
advantage of me.
That changed things quite
dramatically.
That was the small print in the
bottom of the contract you
forgot to read that if I help
you, you help me, not if I help
you, you stab me in the back.
>> PROBST: So, Kenny, did you
get caught trying to work a
deal?
>> Not really because if I felt
like I was going to go that
night, he'd give me the idol,
and of course who else are they
going to vote for but Bob?
It's not called a blindside.
It's called saving me if I feel
like I'm going.
(laughter)
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: So, Kenny, you don't
see any problem with taking it
and then him being vulnerable
and going home.
That's just the way the game
goes?
>> Yeah, that's what he said.
He said he's sacrifice his life
for me if that was the case.
That was the deal.
>> PROBST: Do you really feel
like you need the necklace
tonight or do you just want him
to uphold what you think was the
deal?
>> I feel that I'm safe
tonight, but I still that say we
had a deal and he's not living
up to it.
>> PROBST: All right, it's time
to get to the vote.
Bob, you do have individual
immunity.
The necklace is always yours to
keep or give to somebody else.
>> I think I'll keep it again.
>> PROBST: All right, you
cannot vote for Bob.
Everybody else is fair game.
Susie, you're up.
>> I don't know if this is
really going to be a blindside
or not.
It could be me going home.
I guess we'll see.
>> Susie, I'm really proud that
you got this far.
I hope you the best.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Kenny.
Susie.
One vote Kenny; one vote Susie.
Kenny.
Two votes Kenny; one vote Susie.
14th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury: Kenny.
That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Kenny, the tribe has spoken.
>> Have fun.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
Another blindside and now we
are down to four.
The end is near,
the game, far from over.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> Definitely game over for
Kenny.
And just like in a video game,
sometimes it doesn't go your
way and you lose.
I thought I did extremely well
in this game.
I was playing a lot of people
and in the end I got played
myself and I hope for them the
best.
They got me good.
>> Yeah.
Because it's a reality check.
This is it.
It's all going to depend on who
wins today.
>> This is the last thing you
can do to change your fate,
basically, the last challenge.
>> Today's day 38 and it's huge.
We'll probably have to do an
immunity challenge today, so the
only way I'm going to be able
to save my butt today is I have
to win.
It's almost a given that Bob
will win.
Bob is the wizard and he's
capable of pretty much of
anything.
>> Oh, if I win, I'd vote Bob
off.
It's crazy how Bob's winning
like that.
Just boom, boom, boom.
If I don't win, I know I'm
toast.
I'm just nervous because today
is going to seal our fate and I
look at Bob and Sugar, and I can
see their confidence.
It isn't just luck.
He's pretty skilled.
But there's always a chance that
myself or Matty could pull it.
It may be slim, but I still
have a shot at it.
But if I don't win, I really
feel strongly that I will be
the one going home.
>> Hey, Sue, go get them.
>> Matty went to get tree mail.
>> Here we go.
"Congratulations, final four.
You have done what 14 of your
fellow tribesmen and women
could not.
Today you will honor their
memories.
Go to Exile Island.
There you will find the torches
of your fallen comrades.
At each torch, you will collect
a tribal mask of those who were
voted out before you.
Take them all to the highest
plateau in savannah and burn
them in their honor, as they
each had a part in getting you
to this point.
You will then proceed to your
final immunity challenge."
To be able to pay my respects
to the 14 that went before me
is huge for me.
They were all quality human
beings, quality competitors.
They definitely deserve
respect, and I'm just honored
to be a part of it.
>> Michelle.
>> Very first challenge,
Michelle shocked me.
She did pretty well.
I can't believe the way she
performed.
I wish her the best.
>> This whole experience is
way, way harder than I thought
it would be.
Actually being there and
shivering cold, I was surprised
that I couldn't, like, mentally
overcome that.
>> Gillian.
>> Good old Gillian.
>> I have nothing but good
things to say about her.
She was really fun.
>> What I learned about myself
is that I couldn't compromise
myself in order to fit in
better.
When you're happy, you're
lucky, and you should be happy
that you are lucky in life.
And I'll never lose that.
>> Paloma.
>> Nice girl.
Just as sweet as could be.
Really bright.
>> Survivor has meant a lot
to me, you know?
It changed me.
It challenged me in ways that I
thought I never could be
challenged.
I didn't make it the 39 days,
but at the same time, there is
nothing in this world that can
be thrown at me that I can't
conquer.
>> Jacquie.
>> She's such a nice kid,
always smiling, always helpful.
She should have lasted a lot
longer.
>> I would sum up Survivor as
probably the best experience of
my life.
I think this game definitely
changed me.
I really appreciated being out
there and having that adventure
and I want to continue that in
my entire life.
I want to live that freely.
>> GC.
>> Oh, my God.
>> That kid was classic.
G-Sizzle.
He had a life of suffering and
he said he just didn't want to
suffer anymore.
>> By being volunteered by my
entire tribe to be the leader
was a very important thing to
me.
But I never expected it to be as
difficult as it was.
It definitely changed my life
in 15 days.
Like, I feel that I'm a
stronger person and I know who
I am even more than I did
before I came.
>> Kelly.
I think Kelly did pretty well
in this game, considering her
odds.
She-She made it pretty far.
>> This game has taught me so
much and it made me appreciate
everything, starting from home
and my parents and my life in
general.
And I think it's going to be
with me the rest of my life,
always.
>> Ace.
>> Wow.
>> I feel terrible about Ace
because I took him out, and I
think I took him out too soon
because someone may have lied
to me.
>> He was a shyster, but he was
cool.
>> You know, I think it's
daunting for a person that's
traveled as much as me to be
combined with a group of people
that have traveled hardly ever
out of their county, state,
country, continent.
I mean, it really...
Gave a separation between us.
You have to find common ground,
and I didn't have the capacity
to do that without having a
slightly facetious look on my
face.
>> Good old Dan.
>> I like Dan.
He's a good guy.
>> Yeah, he really had a heart
of gold.
>> He said he came out here to
find himself.
I think he might have pulled it
off.
>> I've always been an
emotional person, and I think,
with this game, I proved to
myself that I have the ability
to calm myself down.
So, I need to take from it what
I've learned and be okay with
that.
>> Oh, Marcus.
>> Marcus.
>> I always thought that Marcus
would be in the top three.
>> I think that playing
Survivor gives you an
appreciation for the way the
world really works and that
there are choices that you make
every day that are good.
There are choices that you make
every day that are bad.
I'd probably stand by my
decision to throw the idol away
because I feel like if it
makes the game less sneaky, then
that's good because I feel like
one of the things that I tried
to do in this game was to not
try and double-cross people.
>> Charlie.
>> Charlie was a wonderful
fellow.
>> He was a great guy.
Charlie was a really sweet
person.
>> I was really surprised with
how, like, patient I was in the
game, how I was able to foster
relationships with people who I
never ordinarily interact with
in real life.
And I'm hoping that when I go
home, I'll be able to have
those skills and integrate them
into my real life and be proud
of who I am.
>> Randy.
>> What I liked about Randy is
he never minced words.
You knew where you stood with
Randy.
>> You know what I've got to
say about Randy?
(blows raspberry)
>> It surprised me because I
was so hated by a good many
people, but I was so well liked
by just as many people.
And I have not felt that
closeness in 20-something years.
I'm not a dumb-ass for falling
for the fake idol.
The people that voted me off
were the dumb-asses.
People screw people and lie to
people.
I played this game honestly,
and Survivor: Gabon has shown
me it's all right to make
friends and it's all right to
like people.
>> Corinne.
She certainly knew how to
tell you what she thought, also.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I've always been the kind of
person that says exactly what's
on my mind and operates without
a filter.
And that is what is sort of
endearing about me in general.
And I think when you take that
away, I'm just another girl who
doesn't have much of a
personality.
Like, just being nice isn't
really a personality trait that
I find interesting.
Anybody can be nice.
>> Crystal.
>> Good old Crystal.
She was the muscle behind
the mastermind.
She got way far.
>> The hardest part has been
knowing that I came so close,
and I didn't succeed.
When you're used to being on
top as a professional athlete,
sometimes it's hard to lose.
But in the end, I failed.
And I think, for me, that has
been very humbling.
>> Kenny, the ultimate
mastermind.
He was the most conniving
player in this entire game.
>> I mean, I think genuinely,
his personality, he really is a
nice kid.
>> He is a sweet kid.
>> He was a threat.
He was underestimated by
everybody.
>> Being out here with random
strangers actually helped me
grow as a person.
I really did step up for
myself.
I really did want to choose my
own path and go with my gut
feeling instead of just staying
back and being scared and I feel
like I've kind of evolved that
way.
Even though I didn't win the
million dollars, I won more
than that because I grew as a
person.
And hopefully people can see
the change in me because I
really feel like I have changed
and for the better.
(singing and playing music)
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
>> You guys ready to get to
your final immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Bob, we'll take it back once
again.
For the last time, immunity is
back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
each have 200 wooden tiles.
On my "go," you will use those
tiles to build a house of cards.
First person to build a house
of cards ten feet tall wins
immunity, is guaranteed a spot
at the final Tribal Council
and you will get a chance to
plead your case for the million
bucks.
Losers go to Tribal Council,
where we will vote out the last
person from this game.
Big enough stakes?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, guys, here we go.
If after 30 minutes, nobody has
built a house of cards ten feet
tall, the person who has the
highest house of cards will win.
For immunity and a guaranteed
spot at the final Tribal
Council, survivors ready?
Go.
It is the first person to build
a house of cards ten feet tall
or the person with the highest
house of cards after 30 minutes
have elapsed.
A lot of different approaches
right now.
Got to make sure your base is
good and stable.
Ten feet is a long way up.
Sugar making a lot of progress.
Is it sturdy enough?
Bob still working to form a
base.
Matty and Bob still hovering
near the bottom.
Susie making a lot of progress.
Susie's house of cards
collapses.
Susie is back to starting over.
Sugar at five and a half feet.
With a big lead, and a
precarious house of cards.
Sugar loses everything and just
like that, after nine minutes
into this challenge, we are
back to square one.
Everybody's in it.
Bob has new life.
Matty has new life.
It's a brand-new challenge.
This could be a million-dollar
challenge for one of the four of
you.
Sugar is once again putting
something up quickly.
Bob getting something going.
Matty continues to work very
methodically.
Susie gaining on Sugar.
Susie now getting closer to the
five-foot mark.
Sugar now up at the six and a
half feet.
>> Oh, God.
>> PROBST: Once again, Sugar's
house of cards completely
collapses.
Susie now in the lead.
Just past the five-foot mark.
Susie loses her house of cards.
Susie now starting over.
Bob loses everything he had.
Matty now in the lead,
taking his time, building
a solid foundation.
Sugar once again in the lead.
Up over six feet.
Susie up over five feet.
Matty up over four feet.
Bob still struggling.
To three feet.
One of the most dominating
forces in this game cannot get
a house of cards going.
We're at 25 minutes now.
>> We have five left?
>> PROBST: Five minutes left.
You have five minutes left to
build a house of cards as tall
as you can, provided nobody
gets to ten feet.
Sugar being careful not to
knock this one over.
Susie not slowing down, now up
at the six and a half feet.
Matty at five and a half feet,
looking very stable.
Bob racing to get in this
at three feet.
Sugar getting close to the
seven-foot mark.
Once again, the big question:
will it stay up?
Susie way up over seven feet.
>> Oh, God.
There is no wiggle room when
you start to get this high.
The person who has the house of
cards that reaches the highest
and will stand up on its own
without the aid of your hands
will win immunity and be
guaranteed a spot at the final
Tribal Council.
Susie at eight feet.
Susie with the lead, and she is
sitting on it.
Matty trying to close the gap.
Sugar trying to close the gap.
You are going to have to hurry.
Your last minute.
Clock is ticking.
Sugar is at seven feet.
Matty a little over six and a
half feet.
Susie at eight feet.
30 seconds left.
Susie is not going to risk
knocking her house of cards
over.
Sugar is still hovering near
the seven-foot mark.
Matty approaching seven feet
with a very stable,
solid-looking house of cards.
15 seconds.
Ten seconds.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Susie wins final immunity,
guaranteed a spot at the final
Tribal Council.
>> Good job, Susie.
>> PROBST: Susie, come on over.
You won the first individual
immunity challenge, now won the
last.
With this around your neck, you
are guaranteed a spot at the
final Tribal Council.
You will get a chance to plead
your case against the jury.
Bob, Sugar, Matty, for you
three, Tribal Council tonight,
where one of you will be the
last person voted out of this
game, the last member of our
jury.
Should make for a very
interesting afternoon.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Congratulations.
>> I did not think I was going
to win this immunity.
I was totally in shock that I
won today.
I just was not expecting that
at all.
I super-needed it because I
knew I was going to go home
today.
So now I'm not going home until
tomorrow.
(chuckles)
>> This is definitely not what
I expected when I got rid of
Kenny yesterday.
I thought that keeping Susie
would be the smarter way to go
because she would never win.
But that's what happens when you
underestimate somebody.
(elephants trumpeting)
>> It's been a good game, guys.
>> You played great.
>> You did, Bob.
>> I wasn't expecting this at
all.
>> I don't know what to say,
Bob.
>> I really, I really thought
tonight was going to be my night
to go home, honestly.
>> Sorry, it was just like...
super emotional.
>> Hey, guy.
>> Appreciate our time out here,
buddy.
>> Yeah, yeah.
Hey.
>> Susie won, and, I mean...
that means we have to vote for
Bob.
>> You been, you been good
players.
>> You friggin' did awesome,
Bob.
>> It's obvious that Bob would
win, so Susie's going to be
voting for Bob.
And, I mean, he knows, he knows
nobody would win against him.
>> Well, it's been a good game.
It's been fun.
Been a good time.
>> I have to write your name
down, Bob, I'm sorry.
>> That's all right.
I-I got no problem.
As Susie always says, it's a
game.
I know what it is, so...
>> You are the best competitor
out here, though, dude.
>> I really thought for sure
you were going to kick my butt,
Bob.
Too many times, I actually
doubt myself.
And I knew this time, I thought,
"You can't have any doubt.
You just have to tell yourself
you're going to do it.
You have to go in there and just
tell yourself you're going to
beat him; you're going to beat
him."
I thought, well, I'm going to
go home tonight for sure.
(chuckles): I really was.
>> You can never count on
anything in this game.
>> Nope, expect the unexpected,
I guess.
I actually kind of shocked
myself.
Like, "Oh, my God, I think I
just did it."
I am the final three.
That is so exciting.
I'm always underestimated.
I... people just think, "Like
she's got a chance in hell that
she'll ever accomplish
anything."
I visualized myself winning it.
Like, I can do that, I can hear
it, it's going to happen.
I did.
It's friggin' insane.
I was not expecting that at all.
I'm, like, in shock right now.
I really am.
I was nervous all day.
I was kind of anxious.
I'm in total shock.
I can't friggin' believe that
just happened.
Hey, Bob, will you be honest
with me?
I'm going to ask you a
question.
You have to be honest with me.
If you were to go with me to
the final three, do you think
you'd get a lot of jury vote?
>> Do you want to go up against
me?
>> Do I want to?
>> Yeah.
>> I-I would rather you just
tell me the truth so I can
kind of know.
>> There's really no point in
even asking the question, you
know.
>> Well, I just, I just...
>> No, there's no point in
asking.
>> I just opened a crack there
for Bob to...
I wanted him to know that I
would have no problem, you know,
taking Sugar out and bringing
him with me.
Had you or Bob won, I would have
been going home.
You can be honest with me.
I mean, I would have been going
home.
>> Let's... how about if we talk
about something else?
We don't need.... we don't need
to talk about this.
You know, you know the score.
We don't have to keep repeating
it.
Let's just have lunch, okay?
>> He snapped a little bit at
me, so I thought, "Okay, you
just sealed your own fate."
>> I'm just in shock.
I wasn't expecting it at all.
>> But I don't think he wants
any constant reminders all day
long that he lost.
>> Don't worry about it.
Just stop talking about it.
>> Okay, all right.
Apparently, I talk too much.
Is it just me, or do I hear
other people talking all the
time, too?
But maybe just, it's me more.
I don't know.
>> You-you talk a lot.
(Sugar chuckles)
You say everything that you're
thinking.
>> That's not, that's not good.
>> Maybe you shouldn't say
anything else about it for the
rest of the night.
'Cause, 'cause it's like, I know
you like to say everything on
your mind.
And if you keep saying, "Oh, I
can't believe it. I can't
believe it," it's just going to
bum him out a lot more.
Say it to us.
Don't say it to him.
Just because... I mean, I-I
really love him, and I just
don't want him to have his
feelings hurt any worse than
they are.
I really, really pictured Bob
up there in the final three.
If I were to vote for Matty and
Bob were to vote for Matty, and
Matty and Susie voted for Bob,
there would be a tie.
>> That would be really nice.
I appreciate that.
>> Okay.
That sounds like a good idea.
Causing a tie is an option
worth considering.
I guess that would be giving
Bob another chance, but I told
Matty I would never write his
name down.
I never promised Bob that.
But to me, Bob is a father
figure.
I lost my dad recently, and
that's probably, you know, why
I-I kind of have the feeling of
love towards Bob.
He's the father figure of our
tribe.
Oh, God.
It is a tough choice because
it's like choosing between my
dad and my brother.
>> Wow, this is huge.
>> Yeah.
>> It's, like, shocking.
I don't even know what to do.
I'm nervous. I'm paranoid.
I'm like... it's such close
grasp, it's just like...
I don't want it to slip through.
>> He knows he's going home.
He's going to be by himself and
try and, like, you know,
meditate or enjoy the last bit
of this.
>> I've talked to Sugar about
the vote tonight.
I'm going to vote for Matty,
and Sugar told me that she'd
vote for Matty, which means
that it may come down to a
tiebreaker.
I don't know whether the
tiebreaker is making fire or
not, but I'm betting on it.
I don't know exactly why Sugar
is being so kind to me, but she
has just been an absolute doll.
I'm packing my bags tonight.
I might go home, but hopefully,
I don't.
Hopefully, um, I stay here in a
ball of fire.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Marcus, Charlie, Randy,
Corinne, Crystal, and Kenny,
voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
Susie, as of this moment, you
are the only person who is
guaranteed a spot at the final
Tribal Council tomorrow night,
who will get a chance to plead
their case against the jury.
What's the feeling right now?
>> I'm very, very pleased and
very proud of myself for
getting to this point.
So I-I just knew if I didn't win
today, I was done.
>> PROBST: On the flip side,
Bob, for the first time in a
long time, you do not have that
immunity necklace, and you are
vulnerable.
>> This is probably the most
uncomfortable Tribal Council
I've been to in 38 days.
>> PROBST: And you got four
former tribe members you were
close to sitting on the jury
right now.
>> People have said to me they
didn't want me on the final
three with them because people
like me.
Um, I am, without a doubt, a
huge threat.
>> PROBST: So knowing you're
vulnerable and you're a target,
what do you do in the few hours
you have between the challenge
and Tribal Council?
>> You know, there's a limit to
how much scrambling I can do.
There's only four of us here.
And I do have a target on my
back, but I'm going to duck at
the last moment if I can.
I don't know how I can do that,
but I'll give it a shot.
>> PROBST: Matty, was it a busy
afternoon when you guys got
back from the challenge?
>> You know what?
Around camp, I didn't really
feel the scrambling as much as
I felt the scrambling in my own
head because when the end is so
close, it's like you don't want
it to slip away.
And at any moment, it can in
this game.
I mean, you never know what's
going on in this game.
No matter how much you think
you know, you don't know
anything.
>> PROBST: Matty, take me
through your options.
You can only vote for Bob or
Sugar.
>> You know what?
Sugar went out a limb for me and
saved me by giving me the
immunity idol, and there's no
way that I could stab her in the
back at this point.
And I can't vote for Susie
because she has the immunity
necklace.
So... my options are limited.
>> PROBST: Bob, you can vote
out Matty or you can cast a
vote for Sugar.
Talk me through your choices.
>> Uh, Matty's well liked by
people on the jury.
He's a-a nice guy.
So I'd be better off going with
Sugar and Susie.
>> PROBST: All right, Sugar,
take me through it for you.
>> I'd lose to both of them.
And I love them both, so I feel
like Matty's kind of like a
brother.
And I feel kind of like Bob is
like a dad.
I feel the same for them both.
>> PROBST: And you have to
choose tonight between voting
one or the other.
Matty, how's it make you feel
to hear Sugar talk about you
like a brother?
>> Feels pretty good.
You know, I look at Sugar kind
of like a sister.
And, uh, when you go through
this with somebody, you develop
a relationship with them.
And if you can endure this game,
you definitely earn my respect.
>> PROBST: Bob, tell me about
your relationship with Sugar.
She referred to you as a father
figure, which is significant in
Sugar's life.
>> I realize that.
I-I feel really good that I've
made that sort of an impression
on her.
I am a father, and I'm, and I'm
a, I'm a damn...
(sobs, clears throat)
Yeah.
>> You're a good dad.
>> I'm a good dad.
(clears throat)
I'm a father, and I'm a damn
good one because I had the best
father anybody could have.
So I had a great example, and I
tried to follow it.
I think I've done a good job.
>> PROBST: So now how hard is
it for you to know that she has
this difficult decision?
She has a father figure and a
brother figure, and she has to
choose one.
She has no option.
>> It is the cruelest situation
that she can be put in, without
a doubt.
Uh, but she's there, and I hope
she makes a good decision.
>> PROBST: Well, the time for
that situation is upon us.
Susie, you have the necklace.
I can't imagine you're giving
it up.
>> Nope, I can't give it up.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Susie.
Everybody else is fair game, and
it is time to vote.
Matty, you're up.
>> I know in a short amount of
time, Bob, you made a major
impact on my life.
And I, uh, truly respect the
game that you've played.
>> Hey, Matty, little love
from my friends.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Bob.
Bob.
Two votes Bob.
Matty.
Two votes Bob; one vote Matty;
one vote left.
Matty.
We have a tie.
In the case of a tie, with only
four people left, we go to a
fire-making tiebreaker
challenge.
All right, Matty, Bob, you can
each take a spot at a
fire-making station.
You each have a flint and steel.
You each have a box of
fire-making materials.
First person to build a flame
high enough that lasts long
enough to burn through the rope
stays in this game, joins Susie
and Sugar at the final Tribal
Council.
Loser goes home.
Clear?
Been out here 38 days.
Making fire is a part of living
out here.
This challenge is on.
Bob has a nice pile of
magnesium.
So does Matty.
Matty's trying to get a spark
using that husk.
Getting a lot of spark, but no
flame yet.
Bob first to get fire.
Bob has a good flame going, but
a lot of that's going to go
away quickly.
Bob trying to hang on to that
flame.
(Matty coughs)
Bob's flame is out.
Trying to bring it back to life.
Bob and Matty fighting for a
spot at that final Tribal
Council and a chance to plead
their case for a million
dollars.
Bob not giving up, trying to
bring it back.
Bob's brought it back.
He's got flame again.
Matty needs to get in this.
Bob has resuscitated his fire,
and he's got a legitimate fire
going now.
Bob doing a good job of
nurturing that fire.
It's getting bigger, stronger.
Bob's got an inferno going
right now.
Flames starting to hit the rope
just a little bit.
Matty still struggling.
Bob has burned through the rope.
Bob has won this challenge.
Bob is moving on to the final
and will have a shot at winning
this game and the million
dollars.
>> PROBST: Matty, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, Susie, Bob, Sugar,
congratulations.
You have gone as far as you can
go in this game.
The power in this game now
shifts to the jury.
Seven people, including Matty,
who you had a hand, either
directly or indirectly, in
voting out of this game, now
hold your fate in their hands.
I'll see you tomorrow night for
your final Tribal Council.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> I've learned more about
myself and about life in the
last 38 days than I ever have.
I grew up quick.
And I'm grateful to have this
opportunity, and I wouldn't
trade it in for the world.
(elephants trumpeting)
(animals grunting)
>> I'm going to mark off day
39, the last day.
>> This is it.
Perfect.
Oh, we did it!
Woo-hoo!
(clapping)
>> ♪ You can do it if you try. ♪
(Susie laughs)
>> We got it.
Day 39.
That's a big day.
Sugar, you want to count them?
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five...
Day 39, and I'm still here.
I-I'm kicking.
I couldn't believe it.
I really just kept believing.
Just-just keep trying.
All you got to do is keep
trying, and if you just focus on
that, you can get through it.
Day 39.
Woo-hoo.
I really just wanted to show,
like, especially my son, what it
meant to try.
And if you just try, you can
make it.
And I did.
I'm here on day 39.
Is that crazy?
It's insane.
We're going to tree mail.
>> Cool.
>> Nice.
>> Yeah!
>> Cool!
>> And batter!
Pancake batter.
Yay!
>> Yes!
Oh, my God, that's exciting.
>> Oh, no mail, just this.
>> Shall we... can you carry
that and I'll carry this?
>> Yep.
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
It's day 39, baby.
We're going to have us a nice
meal.
>> We just got tree mail, and it
was a feast.
So we had a nice brunch.
(laughs)
>> Final three.
Whoo!
>> You guys going to be able to
eat everything?
>> Oh, yeah.
Making bacon.
>> It's really yummy.
>> Oh, my God, it's so good.
I've come a long way, baby.
It's incredible.
Except for Marcus, I pretty
much had something to do with
the ousting of everyone on the
jury.
And that's why I'm scared to
death of the jury.
(laughs)
I mean, geez, they hate me,
but, you know, what are you
going to do?
I might get a jury vote or two.
I hope so.
That'd be nice.
>> Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
Oh, guys, I couldn't imagine
having a breakfast with better
people.
>> Me, neither.
>> Oh, it's going to go, huh?
>> I'm building my last final
gadget.
And that is a, uh, fiery
good-bye to, uh, the Garden of
Eden.
This is why my mother wouldn't
let me play with matches.
(Susie chuckles)
>> You're a bit of a pyro
yourself, aren't you?
>> Oh, yeah.
We just packed the inside of
the hut with pieces of the
other hut, so that we can torch
it and, uh, say good-bye to, uh,
Nobag camp in a, uh, blaze of
glory.
Okay, Susie, let's go.
Time to say good night.
I still got one more major
thing to do in Gabon, and that
is convince the jury that my
behavior, my work, uh, my
participation in this game is
worth winning a million dollars
over Susie and over Sugar.
>> Let's do it. Let's do it.
>> Right...
Right there.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Wow, look at that.
>> Whoa.
>> Whoo!
>> You did a good job, Bob.
(Bob laughs)
>> Holy crap.
>> Look at that, how it's just
coming right down.
Wow!
>> That's how fast
stuff comes and goes.
>> 39 days, just like that.
>> 39 days.
>> Done.
>> Crazy, isn't it?
>> Yes.
>> I am looking forward to-to
going to Tribal tonight because
I really want the truth.
I really think that Sugar did
play a good game.
She took control of the game.
Her name was never written down.
And that was huge.
And I really need to know why
Susie thinks she deserves a
million dollars over the other
two people.
And I want Bob to admit that he
did back out on his deal.
And I want him to admit that,
you know, he's not an honorable
person that he said he was.
>> I genuinely don't like any
of these three people.
I don't think there's much I
could hear from the three
finalists that could change my
opinion of these people except
Sugar.
You know, she's made some
fairly decent moves in this
game.
I don't know what Bob is going
to say, but one thing's for
sure: I'm going to tear him a
new one.
It's simply an opportunity for
revenge, pure and simple.
Revenge.
>> For me, the final words
I say at Tribal...
It's a chance for me to be me.
Right before I was voted out,
I was unable to really let them
have it.
I would like to say the things
that I wish I could have said if
I wasn't on the chopping block.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Marcus, Charlie, Randy,
Corinne, Crystal, Kenny, and
Matty, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Susie, Bob, Sugar,
congratulations.
You have gone as far as you can
go in this game.
The power in the game now
shifts to the jury.
Seven people that you had a
hand, either directly or
indirectly, in voting out of
this game now hold your fate in
their hands.
Tonight they're going to be
gathering information to help
them make a million-dollar
decision.
Here's how it will work: you
will each get a chance to make
an opening statement, why you
deserve to win this game.
The jury will then get a chance
to address you.
Then we vote.
Ready to get started?
Susie, opening statement.
>> I feel I deserve this
because I came into this
just wanting to try.
That's all I wanted: to teach my
son is what it meant to try.
I wanted to teach my students
what it means to try.
So for me, it's very important
that I succeed, just in trying.
On day one, I didn't feel that
confident.
I was really scared.
I was going up against an
Olympic gold medalist, a
doctor, you know, a management
consultant, a #1 video gamer,
the pharmaceutical rep,
the video rep...
I was going up against good
people.
And I'm standing here against
Bob, and I'm not afraid to
stand against Bob.
And so that's why I feel I
deserve it.
Because day one, I wasn't
confident, but day 39, I am very
confident, and I feel very
comfortable telling you guys
that.
>> PROBST: Bob.
>> For 38 days, I'd hope you
wouldn't write down my name.
39, I hope you do.
I played with gusto, with my
heart.
I've played hard.
My game strategy was to come in
here and use my personality, my
survival skills, to make my life
and your lives better while I
was here.
I don't think I outwitted you.
I don't think I outplayed you.
The only thing I did was
outlast you, but I'd just like
to say that you people made
this game one of the most
exciting adventures of my life,
and I feel privileged to have
spent it with all of you, and I
would appreciate it if you
could toss a vote my way.
>> PROBST: Sugar.
>> Uh, hey.
I'm sitting up here because I
feel like I played a perfect
social game.
I surprised myself in the
physical department a couple of
times.
But, um, I had to lie, and
that's part of the game, a
couple of times.
And I had to sacrifice some
innocents and I'm really sorry.
And, uh, 38 days nobody wrote
down by name, but everybody
thought about it.
So, uh, the immunity necklace I
found within 24 hours of my stay
on Exile.
And I didn't play it until the
very end, and I think I've
played a pretty darn good game
for somebody who's physically
weak and didn't know what the
heck I was doing when I started.
I've been a free agent the
whole time.
I was in Kota nine days, ten
days on Exile, two different
tribes at Fang, and then the
merge, so...
I just was in it the whole time
by myself.
But I never sought out an
alliance until I made an
alliance with Bob at the end to
save him because I feel he
deserves to be up here.
And that's it.
Thanks for playing.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: All right, jury, in
a minute you're going to get
your first chance to address
Susie, Bob, and Sugar.
I'll give you a moment to think
about what you want to say.
>> PROBST: All right, jury.
You have waited, some of you a
long time, to get your first
shot at addressing Susie, Bob,
and Sugar.
You can address any or all of
them.
Charlie, you're up first.
Get us started.
>> Hi.
Uh, my first question is for the
ladies.
When Jeff asked us to rank each
other and evaluate our peers,
Susie, you were rated as the
worst of your tribe.
Sugar, you were rated the
second worst of your tribe.
Why do you think we should vote
you the top of the totem pole,
now that we're making a new
peer assessment and give you a
million dollars?
Susie?
>> Because I always knew that I
was going to be underestimated,
but I never gave up on what it
meant to try and that was my
whole lesson for myself, for my
son, for my students.
So, as much as it hurt to be at
the bottom, I still feel that
I'm still trying.
Even right now, I'm still
trying.
That's why I deserve to be
where I'm at, and I deserve to
win this.
>> Great.
Um, Sugar?
>> I don't know.
I don't necessarily think you
have to vote for me, but it
would be nice.
>> Huh. Okay.
Um, now, I have a question for
Bob.
We spent a lot of time
together, and I'm curious if
you feel that all of our
intimate cuddling and spooning
all night long might have been
a little more enjoyable than
you would like to admit?
>> You're a wonderful person.
I like you a lot.
And you're nice and warm at
night.
I don't give a hoot.
>> That's what I wanted to hear.
(laughter)
Thanks, guys.
>> PROBST: Thanks, Charlie.
Crystal, you're up.
>> Sue, if coattail riding is
your strategy, bravo, because
you're a coattail rider.
You rode coattails from day one.
Bob, strategically, the young
lady sitting next to you
remote-controlled you like a
race car up and down Gabon.
You need to tell me something
that you thought of that Sugar
didn't remote-control you to do.
>> Strategy-wise, I would say,
no, I was riding coattails.
I really didn't need to do
anything differently to get
where I'm sitting.
>> And my last question is to
Sugar.
I think we've been aligned
since day ten.
I didn't lie to you, I mean,
even to the littlest things.
"Crystal, do I have any boogers
in my nose?"
I would do a booger check.
I need to know why you voted me
out.
>> Crystal, honestly, it was
because of the way you talk and
treat people.
Even though that's the way you
are, and I like it, you were
bullying people.
So, I know it was strategically
better for you to be up here
with me than Bob, but I went
with my heart, thought that you
would forgive me.
And I believe that you will.
I believe that we'll still be
friends.
>> I ain't got nothing else to
say.
>> PROBST: Thanks, Crystal.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Kenny.
>> Susie, why do you think you
deserve the million dollars and
my vote?
>> I know from the very
beginning, I told you the reason
why I wanted to play this game.
And I told you that you and I
were both underdogs.
I'm just an average, ordinary
housewife who thought I was
never going to get to this
point and I really believed it
when I told you that.
>> Okay, Sugar, I really did
trust you.
I opened up my heart, you know.
You are the first girl I could
really trust.
And hopefully, my dating life
isn't going to be so hard after
this.
But you did really scar me.
>> I'm sorry.
>> And it really hurt.
So I want to know why you
backstabbed me.
>> Okay.
I'm sorry.
I had an alliance, also, with
Matty, and also with Bob, and
literally...
Sorry, Kenny.
I thought you were a bigger
threat than her.
When she took the last
immunity, I had totally
underestimated her.
I truly thought that you were a
bigger threat.
>> For some reason, I don't
believe you.
>> It's totally the honest
truth.
I'm sorry.
>> Okay.
Bob, now that I'm out of the
game, I'm going to go back to
the deal that we made.
The deal was that you won the
next challenge, that you'd give
me the immunity necklace.
So I want to know what happened.
>> When I said that, I intended
to do it.
Assuming that when I said,
"I will protect you," you would
protect me.
Once I became aware of the fact
that you were organizing an
assassination on me, you became
the enemy.
Sorry about that.
>> That was not what I wanted
to hear from you, Bob.
Okay, thanks.
That's it.
>> PROBST: Thanks, Kenny.
Corinne.
(clearing throat)
(sighing loudly)
>> Susie, I have one question
for you, and if you can answer
yes to this question, I will
give you my million-dollar vote.
If you get the money, will you
agree to have your vocal chords
removed?
(laughter)
>> No, because I am a talker.
Sorry.
>> Okay, thank you.
Bob, um...
I adore you.
You know that.
The only qualm I have about
voting for you, you are
somewhat one-dimensional.
I've already met nice Bob and
I've played with nice Bob, and
tonight I want to see nasty Bob.
Make me believe that you don't
like Sugar.
>> I can stand up and say that
Sugar did things that I didn't
like.
When I blindsided Randy with my
fake idol, I didn't feel rude
about that, but I felt horrible
the way Sugar stuck it in his
face afterwards.
But in the last couple of
days...
>> Don't get nice.
I don't relate well to nice
people.
Stay nasty.
>> I'm done.
>> I'll take that.
Sugar, you are an unemployed,
uneducated leech on society.
And the only thing I would vote
to give you is a handful of
antidepressants so that no one
else has to be subjected to
your constant crying anymore,
and maybe if you got some, then
it would seem a little more
sincere when you are crying
about your dead father.
You don't deserve the million.
Thank you, everyone.
>> All righty.
Nice.
>> PROBST: Marcus, you're up.
>> So, guys, as you know, I'm
a physician, and I see people
all the time with health
problems that they might have
avoided had they made different
choices.
Now, Susie, you came to
Earth's last Eden proud to be
a mother and a child educator.
I'm surprised, for someone
coming form those roles, "just
a game" is all it took for you
to shed your obligation to be a
positive role model in the
biggest game of all.
And that's life.
Now, Sugar, I'm assuming that
your father really did pass
away.
>> Yeah, he really did pass
You and I have something in
common.
Both you and I have lost
somebody that was very
important from our family.
What I want to know from you is,
will you use a portion of your
million dollars to honor your
family member as I would have?
And I want to know how.
>> I never even considered
actually winning a million
dollars, but if I did, I would
definitely put some for lung
cancer, but also for children
because that's my favorite
cause, but my dad died of lung
cancer, so...
I don't have any money right
now.
I have $50 in my bank account,
but that's what I would give.
>> We'll see if that's worth
my vote.
Uh, Bob, you are a parent.
My own father taught me about
taking responsibility for my
choices, my decisions, my votes.
You're giving ownership of
your choices and your decisions
and your votes to Charlie, to
Corinne, to me, and what I want
from you is one example of when
you chose to be responsible
for your decisions while you
were out there.
>> The occasion didn't come up
for me to take control.
I mean, I didn't need to.
You people were making good
decisions.
There was no point in me
stepping forward and saying,
"No, let's not do that."
>> Okay.
Well, this will be an
interesting choice.
That's for sure.
>> PROBST: Thanks, Marcus.
Randy.
>> Let me start with Susie.
If 39 days ago, somebody had
told me I'd be standing here
and that you would be sitting
there, I would have told them
they were crazy.
You said at least once that you
felt sorry for me.
Just elaborate on that a little
bit.
If you don't know what
"elaborate" means, that means
tell me a little bit more.
>> Just the way you responded
to people or the way you talked
to them.
And I just didn't understand
that.
And I just thought you're not
happy.
You're sad.
And I genuinely really felt like
I wish I knew how I could help
you.
It's that simple.
>> Okay.
>> I'm truly sorry.
It was not meant to offend or
hurt you.
>> Okay, I'm done with you.
Um, Sugar, the night I was voted
out, you proceeded to roll in
the dirt, laughing
uncontrollably.
Did you not know that I was
going to the jury?
Did you not want my vote?
Did you just figure there's no
way I'm getting it anyway, so
I'll make a jackass out of him?
>> I don't think I needed to do
that because you did that
yourself.
>> That's your answer?
>> Yeah.
>> That's your answer for a
million bucks?
>> Yeah.
You were a jerk.
You were a jerk the whole time.
Sorry.
>> Okay, well...
You lose, too.
>> All right.
>> Bob, again, same question as
I gave Sugar.
Did you not want my vote?
I mean, it was a joke on me.
She laughed...
>> Randy, it wasn't a joke on
you.
It was one of the few strategic
things that I did.
>> It wasn't strategic at all.
You had the votes to get me out
of the game.
This is a chance right now for a
million dollars, and please
don't make me vote for Susie
because she is the only one
that didn't laugh.
>> I was going to use the idol.
I was going to bring it back to
camp and let somebody see it,
think I had the idol and
protect myself from being voted
off.
I didn't mean to embarrass you.
I apologize.
The only thing I can say is,
I was absolutely outraged at
Sugar's behavior, and I went
back to camp and I was pissed.
That's the truth.
>> Okay.
Whoever wins the million,
spend it wisely.
>> PROBST: Thanks, Randy.
Matty, close it out.
>> Susie, tell me why the two
people sitting next to you are
less deserving of the million
dollars.
>> Between both of them, I'm
sure I have faults, too.
Apparently, I talk too much and
I don't keep my promises, but I
know this is a game.
And so, Sugar, I really...
I was very, very disgusted with
what she did to Randy.
That really upset me.
Even though, you know, I feel
Randy can be harsh sometimes, he
didn't deserve to be humiliated
like that.
Bob, when I won the immunity
yesterday...
The immunity challenge, I was
really disappointed in Bob when
he congratulated me right away,
and then we came back to the
hut, and he got angry at me.
He just snapped.
And I was like, "Wow, he's
really short-tempered."
Anytime anybody's won
an immunity, I've always
congratulated them.
I just felt that he could have
felt happier for me because
I did win it.
I really did try and I did win
it.
>> All right, well, good job for
making it to this point.
All right, Sugar, I know you
created this persona of
yourself that's very innocent,
but everybody here tonight
knows that that's total garbage.
I want you to reveal something
that you did that was just evil.
>> Kenny.
I broke Kenny's heart, I feel.
And I let him down.
That hurt, and I'm sorry.
>> That's all you got, really?
All right, Sugar.
And, Bob, basically, all I got
for you, is why the two people
sitting on either side of you
are more deserving of the
million-dollar prize.
>> Um, I don't think they are.
>> All right, well, uh, thank
you for sharing this crazy
adventure with me.
And, uh, good luck.
>> PROBST: All right, jury,
you've had your chance to
address Susie, Bob, and Sugar.
In a moment, you're going to
make a million-dollar vote.
I'm going to give you a minute
to think about that vote.
>> PROBST: All right, Susie,
Bob, Sugar, you've had your
chance to address the jury.
Jury, you have had your shot at
the final three.
It is now time to vote.
Tonight you're voting for a
winner.
The name you're writing down is
the name of the person you feel
most deserving of the title of
sole Survivor and the
million-dollar check that goes
along with it.
For the last time, it is time
to vote.
Marcus, you're up.
>> Susie, you and I were friends
from day one, and we are friends
on day 39.
Spend it wisely.
>> You did an awesome job
surviving in Africa.
I'm just not sure how the hell
you survive in the real world.
>> All three of you, kiss my...
>> PROBST: I'll go get the
votes.
Susie, Bob, Sugar, jury, to all
of you, I say thank you for a
great season of Survivor.
And I will see you back in Los
Angeles for the reading of the
votes.
(audience cheering)
>> PROBST: All right!
Let's do it!
Susie, Bob...
You look nervous, Bob.
(laughing)
And Sugar.
I've got some votes.
A jury of your peers has
decided who they feel is most
worthy of the title of sole
Survivor and a million-dollar
check.
(audience cheering)
Tonight, you want to see your
name.
Usually, votes are bad.
Tonight, they're worth a
million bucks.
It is time to read the votes.
First vote.
Bob.
(audience cheering)
Susie.
One vote Bob; one vote Susie.
Two votes Susie; one vote Bob.
Susie.
>> I can't believe it.
>> PROBST: Three votes Susie;
one vote Bob; no votes Sugar.
>> Ah...
(chuckling)
Bob.
(audience cheering)
Three votes Susie;
two votes Bob.
Bob.
We are tied.
Three votes Susie;
three votes Bob.
If this last vote is a vote for
Sugar, we have a tie.
It is not a vote for Sugar.
Let's go in tight on Susie and
Bob.
The winner of Survivor: Gabon...
(audience cheering)
>> (chanting): Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob...
>> Jeff: WELL, "SURVIVOR: GABON"
BROUGHT US ONE OF THE OLDEST AND
MOST LIKABLE SURVIVORS IN
HISTORY.
BOB THE PHYSICS TEACHER FROM
MAINE IS A MILLIONAIRE.
WE WILL FIND OUT HOW HE MADE
THAT BEAUTIFUL FAKE IDOL.
AND WE WILL ANSWER THE QUESTION,
IS CRYSTAL REALLY AN OLYMPIC
GOLD MEDALIST, AND WE WILL FIND
OUT IF CORINNE AND SUGAR MADE
UP.
IT IS THE "SURVIVOR: GABON" LIVE
REUNION SHOW IN LOS ANGELES.