♪ ♪
>> JEFF PROBST: Tonight on a
special episode of Survivor:
Gabon, you'll get a fresh look
at the survivors with
never-before-seen footage.
>> If you get me, you're-you're
not offended by me.
If you don't get me, you go
crying home to Mama.
>> Oh, my God!
(laughter)
>> Oh!
>> I want to kill Sugar.
I hate her.
>> I'm Sugar.
>> PROBST: For the first time...
>> I'm a professional gamer.
>> PROBST: ...watch the audition
tapes that turned the applicants
into survivors.
>> I need a little pain.
I need a little suffering.
>> PROBST: And follow the
unlikely stories of how the
early underdogs came out on top.
Kenny...
>> It comes down to brains
versus brawn and I'm a huge-time
strategist.
>> PROBST: Crystal...
>> The game is outwit, outlast.
You can't outwit Crystal Cox,
baby.
>> PROBST: Bob...
>> My strategy is to be needed.
That's going to get me further
on in the game.
>> PROBST: Sugar...
>> I'm not too bad at this.
(laughs)
I'm a lot better than I thought
for sure.
>> PROBST: Susie...
>> It's about knowing when to
react.
I mean, I really feel confident
I know when to jump.
>> PROBST: Matty...
>> This is by far the hardest
thing I've ever done.
My whole driving force out here
is Jamie; she's my girlfriend.
>> PROBST: And Corinne...
>> I'm here 'cause I want to
win.
I believe that I'll be in the
top three.
>> PROBST: From the very first
moments of the game, the Fang
tribe set themselves up for
failure with some odd choices
during the schoolyard pick.
>> Susie, come on home!
>> I knew it.
>> I'm going to pick the big
homey with all the game right
there.
>> PROBST: It was immediately
clear that Fang was physically
weaker than Kota and this would
prove to be their demise...
as Fang lost ten out of the next
14 challenges.
Kota wins immunity!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Kota wins immunity!
Kota scores!
Kota!
Kota wins immunity and reward!
This is not even close.
>> I'm starting to lose my
spirit.
I'm starting to lose my hope.
We don't match up to Kota
physically.
mentally.
We don't match up to Kota.
>> PROBST: The Fang tribe
bickered.
>> Eat your rice.
(mumbling)
>> Randy, are you, like, the
leader of the tribe now?
>> Drop it.
>> I don't have to drop nothing,
man.
I can ask you something if I
want.
>> And I can just ignore you
then.
>> PROBST: Michelle, the tribe
has spoken.
And their tribe quickly
dwindled.
Gillian.
>> Bummer.
>> PROBST: Kota lost one member
early on.
Paloma, the tribe has spoken.
But they remained rational and
united.
>> All right, Marcus!
(cheering)
>> Our morale was super high.
We love our team.
>> PROBST: Marcus artfully kept
things together...
>> And away we go.
>> PROBST: ...and made a solid
early alliance with Charlie,
Corinne, and Jacquie.
These four looked poised to go
all the way to the end.
But it's not always the obvious
front-runner that comes out on
top.
Marcus drops a pole.
He's out of the challenge.
And amazingly...
The tribe has spoken.
...out of this early powerhouse
alliance, only Corinne made it
to the final seven.
What are you about to see is the
story of a quiet group of
underdogs who slowly finessed
their games and ended up on top.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
Coming up: we'll get a
never-before-seen glimpse at
the survivors' audition tapes.
>> There's an expression: "That
guy's really out on a limb,"
and, uh... oh...
(growling)
>> Education is incumbent upon
me, but work is something that
has always distinguished me.
>> PROBST: Four months ago, 18
people were chosen to be the
survivors of Gabon.
>> I am 22 years old.
>> I'm going to bring some
entertainment.
>> I've only loved one person in
my life, and that was my dog.
He's in this urn right here.
Dogs rule. People suck.
Uh...
(phone ringing)
I hate (bleep) phones.
>> PROBST: Out of those 18, only
seven remain.
Here's what they said to get
here.
>> And I joined a sorority.
>> Good morning, my name is Mr.
Crowley.
I am a mild-mannered physics
teacher here in Gorham High
School.
There's an expression: "That
guy is really out on a limb,"
and, uh... oh...
(growling)
In order to win Survivor, one of
the things you have to do is be
able to do is eat all that weird
stuff, that real crap.
And I'd like to just thank these
girls here at the cafeteria at
Gorham High School, 'cause over
20 years they've been serving me
real crap, and I think I...
(laughter)
>> Hi, my name is Crystal Cox.
You've probably seen me before,
yes, me, Crystal, the 2004
Olympic gold medalist.
It's time for me to tackle some
new challenges in my life.
Why I think I should be it?
Because I have the three "B"s:
brains, beauty, and blazing
speed.
>> I am 47 years old.
Grew up pretty poor.
Still am pretty poor.
I've always exuded confidence.
I'm-I'm always fun to be around.
Anyway, please call me.
Um, I do want to bring my
tweezers because I don't want
to have a hairy mustache and
a beard when I come home.
That would not be cool.
Okay, got to go.
So, please call me, Mr. Burnett.
I really am ready.
>> I'm from Orange County,
California, and I think I have
what it takes to be on the next
Survivor.
I'm a professional gamer.
Here's some of my checks over
here that I've won doing some of
my tournaments.
What separates me from the
losers are my mind games.
I can out-predict everyone so
well that I'm always one step
ahead of them.
>> Hey, I'm Corinne.
And I'm a graduate of the
University of Florida where I
went on full academic
scholarship, graduated in three
years, and with highest honors.
I've got two tactics.
One: flirtation.
The second tactic is
manipulation.
Oh, and one more thing... I'm a
risk taker.
I always jump into the deep end
of the pool.
>> I'm 29 and I'm Sugar.
I'm jobless and homeless right
now.
Um, my dad passed away five and
a half months ago, and I need to
grow up a lot more than I am
right now.
So, it would be, like, the best
thing that-that I could do for
myself.
I would like to eat some snails
and raw fish and bugs and
whatever it takes and...
Come on in.
>> All righty.
>> Hey, so, I got some company.
Thanks for watching.
>> My name is Matty Whitmore.
I was put on this planet for the
sole purpose of being on this
show.
Matty, Dink, and Jamie.
I love my girl and my boy.
My hard-core physical training.
My hard-core philosophy.
It takes focus and discipline
because living a dream here in
paradise only gets you so far.
I need a little pain.
I need a little suffering.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: 30 days ago, 18
Americans journeyed to a remote
section of Africa for the
adventure of a lifetime.
Welcome to Survivor: Gabon,
Earth's Last Eden.
You guys ready to get started?
>> Absolutely.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: In the very first
challenge, Kota beat Fang by a
landslide.
Kota wins the extra food!
I have corn and beans.
♪ ♪
Kota was upbeat and happy.
>> Rice pudding?
>> Our team rocks!
>> PROBST: But the Fang tribe
was starving.
>> So I don't necessarily think
that that's healthy.
>> It's-it's okay.
Don't even think about it.
Close your eyes.
There's a fruit that we found in
the woods that we call Gabon
pears.
It's rather nasty.
>> It's not bad.
Not bad at all.
>> Little grasshoppers I'm
going to have to call breakfast
this morning, unless y'all want
some.
>> They're all deceased?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Gulping down that grasshopper
was gross.
It was by far one of the
grotesques thing I have ever
done.
He's stuck in my throat.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Anything at Fang that
could go wrong did go wrong.
>> Yeah, it's just a leech.
>> How does the leech look?
I want to see it.
>> No, it's done bleeding.
It used to be bleeding, bro.
It's nothing.
>> Oh, it isn't nothing.
A leech got in the water, you
mean?
>> Yes.
>> Well, it's a good thing you
jumped in and tested it out for
us.
>> Everybody else is scared of
the water now, I think, except
for Matty because of the deadly
leeches that swim out there.
>> You're not worried about
leeches at all, huh?
>> No.
Randy got attacked by leeches
and even though I'm swimming
around in that water, frolicking
around that water, I haven't
seen one leech on me and of
course they grab on to Randy and
suck him dry of all his blood.
(laughs)
It was pretty funny.
>> PROBST: But when he got back
to camp, Matty discovered he
picked up a new friend along the
way.
>> Oh, my...
>> What?
>> I have a leech on my...
>> Oh, you got it on the back
of your ankle.
>> The other side.
>> It was on my freaking cut.
(laughter)
>> That freaked you out.
>> I got it off, though.
>> You better pull your pants
down.
They love your butt, too.
Check that real good.
>> That's disgusting.
>> Look how fat it is.
It grew.
What a scumbag.
Look at all that blood he ate.
>> Oh, man!
>> Let me see. Let me see.
>> All my blood...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: At Kota, Marcus,
Corinne, Charlie, and Jacquie
were running the show, and they
had Bob in their back pocket.
>> I have Jacquie, Marcus,
Charlie, you know.
We're all in your boat.
As long as, you know, you feel
the same way we do, we're all in
it together.
Here's the deal: these are the
four; you're the fifth.
That's all you need to know.
It's the majority; that's it.
So lock it down.
That's it.
>> That's a good point.
>> PROBST: And when Kota won yet
another challenge...
Kota wins immunity and reward!
...they sent Dan from Fang to
be the first to visit Exile
Island.
But this time, Exile Island was
different.
Dan had a choice between getting
a clue to the hidden immunity
idol or spending the time there
in idle comfort.
Dan chose the clue, but his
search for the idol came up
empty.
>> I'm tired.
I'm thirsty, hungry, and I
cannot find this immunity idol.
>> PROBST: At Kota, there was
love in the air.
>> So Marcus and Jacquie always
go off together and have become
the couple of our tribe, which
is a problem.
Because any time you are in a
romantic involvement with
somebody else, it puts a target
on your back.
Honestly, every time you go off
with Jacquie, everyone makes
comments.
>> Do they?
Dude, is that why...?
>> Yes. Yesterday, you guys were
standing at the end of the dock.
They were like, "Do you think
they would agree to just get
married at the end of the dock
right there?"
Yeah, you got some problems.
You need to watch yourself.
I have no intention of staying
with them if they continue
this behavior.
It's just not...
It's bad business.
(hoots)
>> PROBST: When Fang finally won
a reward challenge...
Fang wins reward!
(cheering)
...they sent Sugar to Exile
Island.
>> I knew that.
>> PROBST: How did you know
that?
>> I knew that they were going
to pick me because they think
I'm dumb.
>> PROBST: Some of Sugar's
tribe mates had little faith
she would survive on Exile.
>> She's not going to be able
to find it.
She just... She's a pinup.
Her name's Sugar.
I think Sugar on Exile Island is
doing about as bad as anybody
can be doing on Exile.
She is so, like, clutching her
knees, rocking back and forth,
hysterically crying.
She has an attempted hope for
the idol.
She's probably this close from a
complete meltdown.
If not already in the throes of
a meltdown.
>> PROBST: But Corinne
underestimated the will of the
pinup model.
>> (gasps) Oh, my God, I found
it!
>> PROBST: And just like that,
Sugar had become the most
powerful player in the game.
>> When Fang sent me to Exile,
I thought maybe they thought I
was dumb and that I'd never find
the idol, no way.
I can't believe I found it and
the lawyer didn't.
How funny is that?
That's funny.
>> PROBST: Coming up in a new
scene: an adventure for Kota is
no picnic for Corinne.
>> I'd rather be serving up
poison to these people.
I hate these people.
(bird squawks, rhino snorts)
>> PROBST: When Sugar returned
from Exile, she let Ace, her
closest ally, in on her secret.
>> I just had a very nice
conversation in the canoe, being
told that Sugar has the immunity
idol, and we're going to,
hopefully, dominate this game.
(trumpeting)
>> PROBST: Over at Fang, they
were running out of rice.
>> Seen the rice?
We're over halfway done.
I will... I will make my speech,
and then I'm going to shut up,
and you guys can decide, but we
need to be eating one meal a
day. Period.
We're all going to be hungry.
That's why it's called Survivor.
>> PROBST: With tension still in
the air, good-natured Matty
tried to lighten things up with
a heartfelt song honoring his
girlfriend.
>> Get in a circle around the
fire, okay?
Do you guys want to sing, uh,
"Jamie's a Jolly Good Woman?"
>> Okay.
>> I missed her birthday.
I can't...
I got to do something.
>> You got to sing to her, man.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Is that cool?
>> I like Matty.
He just is a cool kid. He's a...
Reminds me a lot of my little
brother, but sometimes I think
Matty seems a little insecure.
>> Ready, one, two, three.
>> ♪ Jamie's a jolly good woman
Jamie's a jolly good woman
♪ Jamie's a jolly good woman
That nobody can deny. ♪
>> We love you, Jamie!
>> Being out here, it's even
solidified more that I love my
girlfriend, and that's what I'm
doing this for.
>> But I'm realizing that,
overall, dude, I'm
anxiety-ridden.
I got to really address that
issue when I get home.
>> Have you had, uh...
Have you had much tragedy in
your life?
Uh, I mean, everything.
You know, one-one tops the
other.
My dog, Johnson, uh, meant more
to me than any of these people
will.
He's been dead five years, and
I miss him to this day.
And as soon as I get back home,
I'm going to get a new one and
tell him all about being here.
(sniffles)
You know, the dog was five years
ago, and, uh, you know, all I've
done is deal with it.
I'm not the nicest guy in the
world.
I've had a tough 49 years, but,
uh, Matty knows, if you get me,
you're not offended by me.
If you don't get me, you go
crying home to Mama.
(yawning)
>> PROBST: Fang finally started
thinking about alliances when
Matty, Randy, Susie, and Dan
vowed to stick together.
>> We are all totally on the
same page with this?
We don't need to talk about this
anymore.
>> No.
>> Just put it in.
>> We don't.
>> All that matters is the four
of us.
>> PROBST: But at the reward
challenge, all bets were off
when an unexpected announcement
was made.
We are picking new tribes.
>> What?!
>> No!
>> No. No, no, no, no!
>> Oh, wow!
>> PROBST: Drop your buffs.
>> No!
>> Oh!
>> Damn it!
>> I had it all perfect.
Dan, Randy, and Susie and I
solidified our foursome, and I
was super content with it.
I was happy.
I was comfortable with that
foursome.
And then Jeff's, like, "We're
going to switch teams."
And I was just, like, "Oh, no!"
That was just such a buzz-kill.
I didn't even want to hear that.
>> PROBST: Given the opportunity
for Fang to build a stronger
tribe in another schoolyard
pick, they blew it again with
some odd choices.
>> I'm gonna go with Kelly.
I want to get to know her.
>> PROBST: That may be the most
surprising decision in ten days
out here.
>> Of course, the mat gets fully
pulled out from under me, you
know?
It's like the Bad News Bears
again.
We're the goof troop.
>> PROBST: The new red tribe was
Matty, Kenny, Crystal, Kelly,
Jacquie, and Ace.
And the new yellow tribe was
Corinne, Bob, Susie, Randy, Dan,
Marcus and Charlie, leaving
Sugar left standing.
>> What does that mean?
>> PROBST: You will go to Exile
Island.
>> (groaning): Oh, no!
(laughter)
>> PROBST: You will then join
the tribe that goes to Tribal
Council and loses a member.
Since Sugar already had the
hidden immunity idol, this time
she decided to settle into the
shack.
>> Comfort time!
Oh, my God, this is so good.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: At the new Kota
tribe, Randy was trying hard to
keep his aggressive personality
at bay in an effort to secure a
long-lasting position in his new
tribe.
>> I bet you that you're gonna
have to be farther away, though.
>> Susie's doing a great job
around camp, and if Randy has a
poor performance on a challenge,
and he's not really doing that
much around camp, shoot, I'd
rather keep Susie around.
(laughter)
>> Randy.
>> PROBST: And at the immunity
challenge, Randy proved he was
a force to be reckoned with...
(grunts)
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: ...and helped his new
tribe continue their winning
streak.
Kota wins immunity!
>> Yes! Yes! Yeah!
Yeah!
Go, Kota!
>> PROBST: Back at Fang,
Crystal, Kenny, and Matty had to
decide which newly-inherited
member of Kota would go next and
why.
>> I say Kelly.
I think Kelly's the weakest
link.
We were going to vote off Sue
next.
What's the difference in Sue and
Kelly?
Not a damn thing.
>> The difference is, uh, Sugar
may have the immunity idol.
Ace, Sugar, and Jacquie: those
three right now is real deadly.
>> Darn it.
>> You cool?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: That night at Tribal
Council, Crystal's influence
over the tribe prevailed, and
an original frontrunner of Kota
was voted out.
Jacquie, the tribe has spoken.
When Sugar returned to her new
home, the Fang tribe, she was
disappointed that Jacquie wasn't
there.
>> Welcome back.
>> Yeah.
So, that means Jacquie's gone.
>> Yup.
>> That sucks.
(roaring)
>> PROBST: The next day, Corinne
was just as shocked to learn
that one of her closest allies
had been voted out.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: A lot of reactions on
Kota.
Surprised?
>> Yeah.
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: From the very first
days of his adventure, Bob's
fatherly ways and ingenious
craftsmanship were his way to
keep him in the game.
>> It's actually turning out to
be a nice-looking bench.
>> This is the coolest stuff.
>> You're the coolest, Bob.
>> This is a slingshot we're
supposed to kill birds with, but
it also acts as a, uh, Hawaiian
sling.
>> And how many birds have you
gotten?
>> Uh, none.
We're in the middle of the
jungle, and this is my forte,
and they all know it.
I made that tripod to put the
pot on so we could cook with it,
and I made the spoon, made the
spear thing.
>> Marcus, don't you think we...
that would have been nice for a
fish?
>> Yeah, but it's bottom-heavy.
>> I am valuable to them, and
I've grown to like them, and
they've grown to like me.
>> Is that the sun dial?
>> Yeah. It sort of...
>> Show me how that works.
>> It's really neat because I...
They show me a lot of respect.
If we were at the equator, it
would be a right straight line
right over, uh, which we all...
>> So this isn't read like a
clock then?
>> No.
>> Having Bob around is
definitely an asset, but I am
not looking to take him to the
end.
>> PROBST: Coming up: Corinne's
anger gets out of control.
>> I want to kill Sugar.
I hate her!
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Fang's continuous
string of losses and lack of
food began to wear on Crystal's
nerves.
>> 13 grains of rice.
We can all have two grains.
>> Eat your rice.
>> Quit, uh, tell me what I
should be doing out here.
>> Eat your rice!
>> Shut your mouth!
>> PROBST: GC had had enough.
>> You ask to leave this game,
man, and it's... people pounce
on that.
GC is quitting.
>> That's bull.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm voting for GC, hands down.
He's quit at the challenges, and
now he wants to quit the game.
To me, he's a loser.
Being out here alone, starving
is a mind game in itself.
So that's where I stand.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: And that night at
Tribal Council, Matty, Kenny,
and Crystal granted GC his
wish.
The next day, Crystal's
suspicions that Sugar had the
hidden immunity idol were
confirmed when she went digging
through Sugar's bag and found
it.
>> We all know that Sugar has
the... an immunity idol, and it
really changed things because
right now, everybody's scared of
that idol.
>> PROBST: Matty continued to
fight hard for the Fang tribe.
>> We gotta move!
>> PROBST: But his teammates
just didn't have it in them.
Sugar and Kenny both drop out.
Kota closing in on a big win and
a huge reward.
Kota wins reward!
And Crystal broke down in tears.
>> Wah, wah, wah.
>> Randy's just over-the-top.
He's rude.
Randy comes off as a snake to
me, and to me, he's a troll.
>> PROBST: Fang kept on losing.
Kota, you continue to dominate
in this game.
And at Tribal Council, Kelly
was the next to go.
The next day, Sugar dropped the
ball and was sent back to Exile
Island for a record-breaking
fifth time.
And Kota won a big reward.
Should be a fun afternoon.
Kota took a journey to a remote
part of Eden for a lavish
picnic.
>> Let's get our blanket out.
>> Dig into the food.
>> Sardines!
>> Tomato and cucumbers.
>> Oh, wow!
>> Man!
>> We got sardines now?
>> Oh, my God, onions!
>> Oh, my God, Bob got us
sardines.
>> Oh, my God!
>> We've got avocados.
>> Did you ever think we'd be
standing on a cliff in Gabon
sipping champagne in clothing
and underwear we've been in for
18 days, 19 days?
We knew we were going to get
some sandwiches, but that's all
we knew.
>> Chocolate?
>> Chocolate!
>> It turns out it was a very
involved picnic.
This was not your average, like,
schmo picnic.
>> What about this?
>> Those are gherkins.
>> Pickles, those'll last.
>> Yeah, I'd like to have one of
those.
>> They're passing around things
like gherkins, really simple
small pickles.
Nobody knows... "What are
these? Are these African?"
>> This smells like cat food.
>> That's pâté.
>> We use its stink back for
the catfish.
>> No, no, no, it's expensive.
We do not do that.
Who doesn't know what pâté is?
Prosciutto.
"What is Bleu cheese?"
I mean, these are not
non-American or foreign things.
It was maddening.
>> We are so having diarrhea
tonight.
>> At least I'll be drunk.
Maybe I won't remember it.
>> Speaking of drunk,
who's-who's on the next bottle?
>> What is this-- the deal with
this bottle?
>> I think you have to do it
with... by bottle.
>> I don't think... you guys
own that bottle between the two
of you?
>> No, no, they don't.
>> I don't care.
>> It becomes less enjoyable
when you have to worry about
divvying everything up because
everybody's always conscious of,
"Is he getting more?"
>> Randy's sucking it down.
>> Unfortunately, you get these
great experiences, but you have
to share them with people you
can't stand.
I-I'd rather be serving up
poison to these people.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Sugar spent so much
time on Exile Island that after
finding the idol on her first
trip, her biggest enemy in the
game was boredom, but she found
ways to stay occupied.
>> I got sick of wearing a
leopard dress, and, uh, I don't
have any other clothes, so, uh,
I'm looking kind of crazy these
days.
This is my Mary Ann look.
Do you like it?
>> PROBST: When she was tired,
she'd hit the hammock.
She spent her days picking
flowers and berries; basking in
the sun in her own private Eden
was a joy.
She even had her own swimming
pool.
But nothing was better than
biting into the apple of Eden.
>> I'm so happy.
(laughs)
I could cry.
>> PROBST: And she did.
She actually felt guilty about
her good fortune.
>> Why do I get to come back
here and-and eat fruit when
everybody's starving at my
tribe, and they're running out
of food.
I'm feeling really guilty.
>> PROBST: Sugar's many days on
Exile kept her out of the
politics of camp and helped her
transform from an inexperienced
girl to a power player.
>> I learned that I may be a
little tougher than I thought.
I maybe have underestimated
myself.
Exile Island wasn't so bad for
me.
>> PROBST: The next day, a
surprising announcement was
made.
Bad news is both tribes are
going to Tribal Council tonight.
The good news: each of you
will have an equal shot at
winning... individual immunity.
Marcus won individual immunity.
Congratulations.
And had the power to give
another immunity necklace to
someone from the other tribe.
>> I'm going to give this to
Sugar.
>> PROBST: Sugar found herself
doubly protected with
individual immunity and the
hidden idol.
Sugar is safe at tonight's
Tribal Council for Fang.
Marcus is safe for Kota's.
Back at camp, Kenny's mind games
came into play when he lied to
Sugar about her strongest ally,
Ace, wanting to blindside her.
>> Honest to God truth, this is
what's happening around camp.
I'm not... I'm not lying to you.
Ace thinks he has you wrapped
around his finger.
This guy is a snake.
We blindside Ace....
>> Blindside Ace tonight.
>> ...and we don't have to worry
about the snake ever again.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Sugar bought the lie,
and it was Ace who was
blindsided at Tribal Council.
♪ ♪
At the Kota Tribal Council, Dan
was voted out.
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
When the tribes came together
for a feast...
>> This is nuts!
>> PROBST: ...they assumed the
merge had come.
During the meal, Kenny spotted
a clue.
>> What?
>> I feel like you guys should
take a look, too.
>> What does it say?
>> "You have just discovered a
clue to another hidden immunity
idol."
>> PROBST: But no one wanted to
take the idol for fear of
seeming too aggressive.
>> It's the apple in the garden
of Eden.
>> Yeah, you want the apple,
take it, but no...
>> PROBST: So in the end, the
tribes did the unthinkable.
>> One last time, anybody who
wants immunity, it's theirs.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Who wants it?
>> The ocean wants it.
>> The ocean!
>> PROBST: Randy and Marcus were
so confident that they ditched
the one thing that could save
them.
>> These people are so stupid.
I got ten people to throw an
immunity idol into the ocean.
It's never been done.
>> With all due respect to
President Bongo, I am the new
king of Gabon.
I'm sorry, but I rule.
This ocean-- it's mine.
>> PROBST: And just when they
thought a merge was on the
horizon...
>> Oh, man.
>> Number one...
>> Here we go.
>> PROBST: ...they found another
switch was in store.
>> The new Kota tribe is Bob
and Marcus and-and Susie,
Crystal and Kenny.
>> I'll see you.
>> The new Fang tribe: myself,
Charlie, and Corinne and then
we've got Matty and Sugar.
>> PROBST: At Fang, Matty told
Sugar she was duped by Kenny.
>> Wow!
>> Ace was covering you the
whole time.
>> I know. I know.
>> He never was gunning for you.
>> I didn't know.
I think Kenny and Crystal duped
me.
I feel awful that I got rid of
Ace.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: At the next immunity
challenge, Matty's inner
strength and physical stamina
single-handedly won a heroic
victory for Fang.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Matty wins immunity
for the Fang tribe.
Facing Tribal Council, Marcus
was confident and acted like he
was still in control of the
game.
>> I don't want you to go home.
And know that Susie is going to
campaign for it, and the only
way that I feel like we can make
the switch would be to have Ken
go home and you stay.
>> Marcus and I now have a
solid relationship, but when you
start talking about knocking off
my number one ally, just so you
can go farther in the game, I'm
not pleased at all.
>> PROBST: Then Marcus had a
chat with Susie.
>> My thought was tonight Ken
and then, if hopefully we don't
have to go for a while, but then
Crystal will be next.
>> PROBST: But Crystal told
Kenny about Marcus's plan.
>> What do you mean?
What do you mean?
>> PROBST: And all of sudden,
Susie was the key.
>> I have a huge decision to
make tonight on which way to go,
either Marcus or Bob, or I can
vote with Kenny and Crystal.
>> PROBST: And that night at
Tribal Council, the person
responsible for dumping the
idol now needed it and was
voted out.
Ninth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon, and the first
member of our jury....
Marcus.
At the next reward challenge,
Fang was in shock that Marcus
was gone.
>> He didn't deserve to leave
the game.
>> PROBST: And Kenny's
confidence was growing.
>> Then who does?
Who does deserve to leave the
game?
>> I could not believe they had
gotten rid of Marcus.
It was so heartbreaking, just
because that really damages my
chances at the game.
>> PROBST: But Fang won the
challenge.
>> Hey, we won!
>> PROBST: And Bob was sent to
Exile Island.
Bob, grab your stuff.
(shouting)
Matty and his tribe enjoyed
some real African culture and
food at a local village in
Gabon.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: While over on Exile,
Bob searched for the idol, not
knowing that Sugar already had
it.
>> The fourth clue got me
completely perplexed.
>> PROBST: Bob decided he
couldn't leave Exile Island
empty-handed, so he made his
first major strategic move.
>> I'm going to make something
that looks like an idol so that
they think I have an idol.
Sort of like when you're
holding up a bank.
You don't necessarily need the
gun, but if they think you've
got a gun, they might leave you
alone.
This is my new fake idol.
>> PROBST: Coming up, Randy
stirs up trouble around camp.
>> Desperate times, man, call
for desperate measures.
>> Shut up, Randy.
You're being a lunatic.
>> PROBST: At the next immunity
challenge, the merge was finally
announced.
Your merge.
>> Oh, wow!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: And Susie surprised
everyone by winning immunity.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Susie wins immunity!
Back at the newly merged camp...
>> People bounced into the
jungle and started their
strategies.
>> PROBST: ...Charlie and Randy
were gunning for Crystal.
>> Crystal's the way to go.
Bob will vote Crystal.
>> PROBST: With Sugar in the
middle, Corinne and Charlie
tried to convince her to vote
with the old Kota.
>> Yeah. I'm...
>> We can do Randy next.
>> PROBST: What Charlie didn't
know was that Matty, Susie,
Crystal, and Kenny had a
different victim in mind.
>> This is some real.
This is the realness over here.
>> Write down Charlie.
Write down Charlie.
>> Charlie, Charlie, Charlie.
>> PROBST: And Kenny tried to
pull Sugar over to his side.
>> Charlie is the brains behind
all of it.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Knowing the vote was
in her hands, Sugar had to
decide whether to go with her
old tribe or her new allies, who
promised to take her to the end.
And that night at Tribal
Council, Sugar's vote sealed the
deal, and the early underdogs
suddenly became the clear
frontrunners in the game.
Tenth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon...
Charlie.
With Charlie gone, Bob, Randy,
and Corinne found themselves in
the minority of a tribe led by
Sugar.
>> Even though I don't like the
way you've been talking--
negative and everything--
I thought maybe you could learn
from me by telling you
and-and...
>> Let your countenance be your
light.
>> Yeah, a little bit.
I know that sounds stupid,
though.
>> But that's how some people
need to learn.
>> Right, so I'm just letting
you know that I hate the way
you've been, but-but I know that
you're not a bad person.
You just got a little out of
hand.
>> So this morning, I'm in the
hut, and Sugar decides that
she's going to teach me a
lesson about life.
>> We had one good conversation.
The rest the time, it was you
and Randy talking about
everybody else.
And it's just...
It's a negative way of being,
and it was happening so much,
I was just like, "Oh, my God.
It's like cancer in my ears."
It's, like, all the complaints.
Nothing was good enough.
It was horrible.
Okay, I don't want to keep
harping on it.
I just want you to realize that
everything that you say is-is
noted, you know, and-and...
>> All right.
>> You know?
Okay, cool.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to...
to talk to you about it.
>> From a girl who is-- I'm
sorry-- a non-college-graduate
waitress who's out of work.
She doesn't even have a waitress
job.
She lives off the "kindness" of
others.
I don't like people that live
off the kindness of others.
There is no honor in that.
Just more like a second to vent.
I want to kill Sugar.
I hate her.
>> She's horrible.
>> You don't understand.
She pulls me into the tent, and
she's like, "I know that you
were making fun of me, and I
know what you and Randy said,
and you don't even know me, and
I want to teach you about
forgiveness and about how being
nice to people is better than
being mean."
So I was, like, "You know, I
don't have any friends.
You're the only person I have
left."
I'm sitting there, like,
cringing.
Like, "Really, bitch, you're
going to teach me something?
I'm gonna teach you something."
>> She's the worst person in the
world.
It's people like that that are
so self-righteous...
>> Oh! Oh, my God!
>> ...and high-and-mighty that
are a million times more evil
than me.
>> My favorite... My favorite
is, like, she's so stupid...
>> That it's dangerous.
>> Yes! And I'm just, like...
I never complained.
She's the one who keep...
She's always complaining about
where she sleeps.
She's complaining about where
she's sitting.
I won't... I can't even...
I just...
You don't understand.
All that gets me through the day
is, I've rehearsed the speech
I'm gonna give after they say
my name at Tribal.
I'm gonna turn on her and be,
like, "You know what the best
part about going home is?
I don't have to pretend to like
you anymore."
>> Exactly.
>> I'm gonna be nasty at Tribal.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Oh, there.
Go, go, go, go.
At the very least, I have the
jury.
We'll give the million to who
we want to give the million to,
and trust that won't be Sugar.
I don't know who it will be,
but it won't be Sugar.
So, her little teaching me a
lesson?
Really?
This is how the lesson goes,
bitch.
>> PROBST: Now with no alliance
left, Bob showed Sugar his only
asset.
>> I couldn't find it anywhere.
I made a fake one.
>> Oh, my God.
That's awesome.
>> PROBST: At the next reward
challenge, a Survivor auction
was full of surprises.
If you see something you like,
you should bid on it.
>> "Send yourself or someone
else to Exile Island."
>> Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
>> I'll take Bob.
I'm sorry, Bob.
>> PROBST: Bob, get your
personal items.
You're going back to Exile
Island.
You will return in time for the
next immunity challenge.
And Randy thought he'd soften
his image with a plate of
cookies.
>> $20.
>> PROBST: Sold to Randy.
>> Oh, my God, Randy.
>> Would you like one?
>> I couldn't possibly.
>> PROBST: But Sugar couldn't
hide her dislike for Randy.
Randy, you're giving Sugar's to
Corinne?
>> Sugar doesn't have one.
I offered her one, and she
didn't take one.
>> PROBST: But he couldn't charm
Sugar.
>> Last chance.
You can have a full one.
>> PROBST: And he lost his last
cookie when Sugar snatched it up
and gave it to Matty.
>> That cookie's tainted.
>> PROBST: Back at camp, Randy
just couldn't let it go.
>> That wasn't a gift from her,
man.
That was my cookie.
I didn't get one.
You had two.
I had none.
>> Sorry.
>> I left the auction half
drunk and pissed off.
>> PROBST: Unaware that Sugar
had the hidden immunity idol,
Randy bet on Bob finding the
idol at Exile and giving it to
him, so he cooked up a
last-ditch scheme with Corinne.
>> FYI, I'm going to be crashing
and burning all day, making
everybody miserable.
Our only prayer is if Bob would
give me the idol.
>> I love it.
>> It's our only prayer.
>> That's a great plan.
>> PROBST: Randy purposefully
made himself irritating to get
people to vote for him.
(Randy imitates yawning)
>> Oh, my God, don't do this,
dude.
Don't.
>> What are you going to do,
vote me out?
Desperate times, man, call for
desperate measures.
>> Shut up, Randy!
You're being a lunatic.
>> Well...
>> Be nice, bro.
>> I got to do what I got to do.
There's not a normal person
among these idiots, except you,
and you even whored yourself
out.
You know you have.
You know, I don't blame you.
It's worth a million dollars to
you.
It's not to me.
>> Oh, my God.
(Randy laughing)
>> It's a no-brainer that Randy
has to go home now, so
everybody's a little paranoid
today about him burning the
camp down, dumping our food,
ravaging people's personal
items.
>> I'm just scared he's going to
dump out the coffee, throw the
beans and rice into the woods,
or whatever.
>> Yeah. He's just not happy
right now.
>> But he dug his own grave.
There's a reason he's leaving.
>> You just got to keep an eye
out.
>> I don't know why he's still
here.
>> I can't even believe he's
still here.
>> Well, first we have to beat
him at this challenge.
>> I think he's crazy.
I think he might be crazy.
>> This is ridiculous.
>> Uh-uh.
>> Randy got to go.
Randy needs to go.
He is a troll.
He is wreaking havoc in the
Nobag tribe.
>> PROBST: The next immunity
challenge turned up the
pressure on Randy.
Kenny wins immunity!
With Randy on his last legs,
Bob was his only hope.
>> PROBST: Bob put out the bait.
>> PROBST: And Randy bit down...
>> I'm here for three more days.
Looks like an idol to me.
>> PROBST: ...figuring he had
the game in his pocket.
>> I cannot wait to see this.
You are awesome.
>> PROBST: And that night at
Tribal Council, Randy smugly
made his last move.
But the joke was on him.
This is not a hidden immunity
idol.
(laughter)
And he was the 11th person
voted out of Survivor: Gabon.
Randy, the tribe has spoken.
Well, after tonight's Tribal
Council, it's very clear this
game is coming down to one
thing: trust.
Can't wait to see how it plays
out.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episodes.
>> PROBST: Where 18 once stood,
only seven remain.
How will Sugar cope being in
between good...
>> You, me and Sue to the end.
>> PROBST: ...and evil?
>> I'm not trying to buy your
vote!
I've never been trying to buy
your vote.
>> PROBST: What new adventures
will the survivors face?
What future surprises are in
store?
>> Oh, my God!
(overlapping chatter)
>> PROBST: Join us as the
adventure continues.
>> Look at them boys.
(whistles)
(laughter)
>> Look at Marcus' cute butt.
>> They're all naky.
>> Ow! Ow!
(laughter)