>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Despite having three of the
strongest players in the game,
including a former Olympic
athlete, the Fang tribe lost
three challenges in a row.
Fang is walking, literally
walking!
They thought they could turn
things around by picking GC to
be their leader.
>> If I was volunteered, I'll
take it.
If they want me to roll with
it, I mean, I'll do it.
>> PROBST: But he quit after
one day.
>> We don't need a damn leader.
I'm younger than all y'all, so
what I'm being the leader for?
>> PROBST: The Kota tribe was
on a roll.
They were hard-working and
upbeat.
>> I don't envision us losing
ever.
>> PROBST: So it was a shock to
everyone...
Fang wins reward!
...when Fang finally won a
challenge.
(cheering)
They sent Sugar to Exile
Island...
>> Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God!
(shrieks)
>> ...thinking she was so weak
she'd never find the
hidden immunity idol.
>> Oh, my God, I found it.
Okay, I'm going to cry.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: Sugar kept the idol
secret from everyone except her
closest ally Ace.
At the next immunity challenge,
Fang won again.
(cheering)
Fang wins immunity!
In their first trip to Tribal
Council, Kota demonstrated
their tribe unity by voting out
their smallest and weakest
player in a landslide.
Paloma's lone ally was Kelly,
who voted for Ace.
Paloma, the tribe has spoken.
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Well, that kind of sucked.
I don't really want to do that
anymore.
>> I really didn't like that.
>> Me, neither.
>> We just got back from Tribal
Council.
Paloma got voted off.
I definitely lost a partner in
the game who I can, like, talk
to about things.
And now I'm worried about
the chopping block.
But things can change all the
time.
My strategy right now is I
want Ace off.
I just don't like Ace.
>> How do you feel about Tribal?
How was it for you?
>> It was a bloody godawful
experience.
Tribal Council was probably one
of the most un-pleasurable
things I have done in recent
history.
It was, uh, right there with my
wisdom teeth being pulled.
That was not fun going there.
>> No.
>> I didn't know she had that
much pent-up animosity towards
me.
>> I didn't, either.
>> I think Kelly voted for me,
and, uh, she will be the next
lamb to the slaughter.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(hippopotamus grunts)
>> Do you think I could try
cooking some sweet rice?
>> Have you seen the rice?
We're over halfway done.
>> We-we should be eating one
meal a day right now and...
Uh, I will, I will make my
speech, and then I'm going to
shut up, and you guys can
decide.
But we need to be eating one
meal a day, period.
We're all going to be hungry.
That's why it's called Survivor.
The rice, quite simply, is
running out.
Strategically, I know that
Crystal, Kenny, and GC are not
with me.
They hadn't listened to a word
I've said since I've been here.
>> I'll catch up with you guys.
Matty, Susie, and Dan, they're
not my allies, but they're my
friends.
And I'm just not sure how to
play it right now.
>> I ain't never seen Dan go
pick fruit a day since we've
been here, and all of a sudden,
he going to go pick some fruit.
>> Exactly.
They're going to go talk right
now.
They got four r-right now.
There's three of us here.
>> That's four.
>> And there's four there.
So they could be trying to do,
you know, something right now.
All I know, it seem like the
tightest three is right here.
>> Those three alienated me
from the beginning.
>> Th-They alienate everybody.
>> I could tell GC the sky is
blue, and he's gonna argue with
me.
>> Matty's having a hard time
with Crystal, and I'm having a
hard time with Crystal.
>> She's hard for me to deal
with.
>> And Kenny, he-he's like
Mini-Me to GC.
>> And then GC is given and he
accepts the role as leader, and
he flails and he gives it back.
>> We have a cancer, and this
cancer's name is GC.
And at the right time, this
cancer is going to have to be
cut out.
We are all totally on the same
page with this.
>> No matter what, Susie.
>> No matter what.
>> I finally feel like I've
solidified my four with Dan,
Randy, and Susie.
And I really, truly feel that
this alliance that I've-- we've
created is going to be solid for
a while.
Think it's going to carry me
pretty far.
>> We don't need to talk about
this anymore.
>> No.
>> Just put it in.
>> All that matters is the four
of us.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Kota, come on in.
Fang getting your first look at
the new Kota.
Paloma voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
You guys ready to get to it?
>> Yeah.
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: You've been out here
ten days, know each other pretty
well.
Now we're going to put that
knowledge to use.
Today, you are going to rank
your tribe from top to bottom
according to importance in your
tribe.
One would be the highest
ranking; you'll work your way
down.
Once you're finished, I'll have
you take your spot according to
rank on the colored pedestal.
Got a tally board for each of
you.
Don't unwrap these yet.
You will fill these out in
private.
Find a spot on the beach, get
started.
>> PROBST: All right, this is
how you guys ranked yourselves
in terms of importance.
The person that Kota ranked as
the most important on their
tribe is Marcus.
>> I'm totally shocked to be
ranked number one.
I was just happy that they felt
that way about me.
On the other hand, are they
going to start thinking that
maybe that's a threat that
needs to be, uh, moved off to
the side as quickly as possible?
>> PROBST: Person voted
second-most important on
the Kota tribe: Ace.
Third: Bob.
Fourth: Charlie.
Fifth for the Kota tribe:
Jacquie.
Sixth: Corinne.
The seventh: Sugar.
Leaving Kelly as the least
valuable member of the tribe.
Kelly, how's it feel?
>> It's interesting.
Being the last one.
I've never been the last picked
ever, so it's kind of different.
>> Kelly's devastated.
"Why am I picked last?
Why is everybody not kissing my
ass?"
'Cause you're a whiny little
cow, and, um... you don't do
anything.
>> PROBST: On the number one
pedestal for Fang: Matty.
Second on the Fang tribe: Dan.
Third: Randy.
Fourth: Crystal.
>> What the hell?
I'm out there busting my butt,
and then they're going to rank
me number four after someone who
can't even barely walk and
barely do anything, and all he
does is sit around and fuss and
curse everyone?
I was very insulted when I saw
that.
>> PROBST: Fifth for the Fang
tribe: Ken.
Sixth: GC.
>> Wow.
Kenny got picked before me?
Damn, this is, this is not
looking too good.
(chuckles)
Yeah, this is not looking too
good for a pimp out here.
>> PROBST: Leaving Susie as the
least valuable tribe member.
So this is it.
This is how you guys ranked
yourselves.
Marcus, any surprises to you on
the Fang tribe?
>> I'm surprised Randy is up as
high as he is.
I really thought that we'd see a
girl in the top two or three on
their tribe.
So that comes as a surprise.
>> PROBST: Randy, you're
getting a sneak peek inside the
Kota tribe.
What kind of insight do you
take from this?
>> I really don't think
anything.
>> PROBST: Really?
>> I mean, this shows
friendliness; this shows
physicality in, uh, challenges,
but it doesn't show a thing
about who's hooking up with who.
>> PROBST: All right.
Well, now you're going to take
all this insight and put it to
good use because we are picking
new tribes.
>> What?!
>> No, no, no.
>> Oh, no.
Oh, wow.
>> PROBST: Drop your buffs.
>> No!
(groaning)
>> I had it all perfect.
Dan, Randy, and Susie and I
solidified our foursome, and I
was super content with it.
I was happy.
I was comfortable with that
foursome.
And then Jeff's like, "We're
going to switch teams."
And I was just like, "Oh, no."
That was just such a buzz-kill.
I didn't even want to hear that.
>> PROBST: Here's how it is
going to work.
Marcus and Matty, because
you were voted the most
important person in your tribe,
you will remain members of that
tribe.
You will be captains, and you
will get us started on picking
new tribes.
Marcus take a spot on the Kota
mat.
Matty, take a spot on the Fong
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: Kota will choose
first.
Marcus, you're now going to
choose somebody from the Fang
tribe.
Who are you going to select to
be your first tribe member?
>> I'm going to take Dan.
>> PROBST: Dan joins Marcus on
the new Kota tribe.
Matty, make your first
selection.
You're choosing somebody from
Kota.
>> I'm going to take Ace.
>> PROBST: Ace joins Matty on
the new Fang tribe.
All right, Dan.
You are now choosing somebody
from Kota.
>> Charlie.
>> PROBST: Charlie joins his old
teammate Marcus and his new
tribe member, Dan.
>> I am thrilled to be with
Marcus.
My biggest fear in this game is
that Marcus and I would separate
because we have each other's
backs, like...
I just love Marcus.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: Ace, you are now
choosing somebody from the Fang
tribe.
>> Since she beat me up so bad,
Crystal, come on down.
>> PROBST: Crystal, first woman
selected.
Charlie, you are now choosing
somebody from Fang.
>> Randy.
(clicking tongue)
>> PROBST: Randy on the new
Kota.
>> PROBST: Crystal, you are
choosing somebody from the Kota
tribe.
>> I'm going to go with Jacquie.
>> PROBST: Jacquie joins
Crystal, Matty, and Ace.
Randy, you are now choosing
somebody from the Kota tribe.
>> Corinne.
>> PROBST: Corinne joins Marcus
and Charlie, Dan, and Randy.
Jacquie, you are now choosing
somebody from the Fang tribe.
>> I'm going to go with Ken.
>> PROBST: Ken joins Matty,
Crystal, Ace, and Jacquie.
All right, Corinne, your choice.
Are you choosing somebody from
Fang.
You have only two choices:
GC, who was ranked number six,
or Susie, who is ranked last.
>> It doesn't matter who they
pick; it's a game.
>> PROBST: All right, Corinne.
I hope the information you're
getting is good info.
>> Well, I don't want to be the
only girl, so we're going to
take Susie.
Come on over.
>> PROBST: Corinne chooses
Susie, leaving GC as the last
remaining member of Fang.
GC, nobody chose you.
>> Well, it's cool.
You know.
It doesn't feel good.
But the last few days have been
pretty hard for me, and I think
I probably rubbed a few people
the wrong way.
>> PROBST: All right, Ken,
you're now making a selection.
You're choosing between three
remaining Kota members, Bob,
Sugar, and Kelly.
>> I don't know Kelly.
>> No?
>> PROBST: Bob still left up
there.
Bob, a little surprised?
You were ranked so high by your
own tribe, and yet nobody's
chosen you?
Are you a diamond in the rough?
Are they missing some gold here?
>> Um...
I think so, but that...
You know, time will tell.
>> PROBST: All right, Ken, make
your choice.
>> Jeff, for myself, I've always
been last picked sometimes and
I know how it feels to be left
out, so I'm going to go with
Kelly.
I want to get to know her, and
she's hot.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: That may be the most
surprising decision in ten days
out here, Ken.
Susie, you're choosing between
Bob, ranked the third most
valuable tribe member, or
Sugar, ranked next to last.
>> I'm going to go with Bob.
>> PROBST: Finally, Bob joins
Susie, Marcus, Charlie,
Corinne, Dan, and Randy.
>> PROBST: Kelly, you have one
choice.
>> G-Sizzle.
>> G-Sizzle!
Come back home.
>> PROBST: GC joins Kelly,
Matty, Ken, Crystal, Ace, and
Jacquie.
The new Fang tribe, which
leaves you, Sugar.
>> What does that mean?
>> PROBST: You will go to Exile
Island.
>> Aah!
>> Oh, no!
>> PROBST: You will remain on
Exile until after the next
Tribal Council.
You will then join the tribe
that loses a member, evening us
up at 7-7.
Ready to head to Exile?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Here is a map.
Not that you don't know the way.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: It's going to be a
long stay out there, Sugar.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: Kota, new tribe
buffs.
Fresh, clean.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Fang, new tribe
buffs.
All right, we have our new
tribes.
For some of you, this is a
brand-new start.
For others, it could mean the
end of your game.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> You guys, this is your new
home.
Feel comfortable.
>> Welcome hone, guys.
>> You guys are really going to
like it here.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I'm so happy.
>> Look at this.
>> This tribe has a completely
different personality.
If Matty was here, it would be,
like, the perfect tribe.
>> The new Kota tribe is four
Kota members: Bob, Marcus,
Corinne, and Charlie;
three old Fang members: Susie
and Dan and me.
If Kota loses the next
challenge, I do think the
original Kota will stick
together and pick one of the
three Fang members off.
If it's not me, I'll go along
with it.
If it is me, I'll burn the camp
down.
>> This is unbelievable.
It's, like, the most comfortable
thing I've sat on in a week.
>> Bob works in his sleep, too.
He wakes up every hour.
>> Yeah, Bob wakes up in the
middle of the night and builds
stuff.
He's going to build us some
bunk beds, I think.
>> Unbelievable.
>> He's awesome, Bob.
The Kota tribe has it together.
They're just functioning really
well.
I see Bob is their worker, and
I think Marcus and Corinne and
Charlie, they really appreciate
that.
So, my strategy right now at
Kota is to just keep working
hard at camp.
And I'm hoping that they see
that as a positive and say,
"She's worth keeping."
>> Comfort time!
When I got to Exile, there was
a choice between comfort and
the clue.
And I already have the idol, so
I chose comfort.
Home, sweet home.
I walked up to my Sugar shack.
It was like Christmas morning.
There was pineapple and oranges
and apples and coconut.
Oh, my God.
This is so good.
(laughing)
(sighs)
This game is so crazy because
I don't know what team I'm going
to be on when I get back.
I'm hoping that I go back to
Fang, so that I can be with Ace.
And hopefully they'll vote off
Kelly, and then I can come take
her spot.
I'm sure they will.
They're not idiots.
>> All right, guys.
Welcome to Fang!
>> I like it.
>> This is our home.
>> Is it different than your
guys' house?
>> Yeah.
>> Really?
>> I mean, the hut looks
similar.
>> This tribe switch is great
for me.
I still got four people of my
original tribe, and I think it
is great, you know what I mean?
I don't think I could be in a
better position right now.
>> If we walk around and pull
ginger, you can cut the root
and you can put it right into
the rice.
>> Yeah.
>> Same with the watercress.
>> Oh, yeah, and ferns.
>> We can't find the ginger.
>> Oh, I can show you it.
>> Oh!
Thank you! Thank you!
>> Yeah.
>> Because you guys didn't
really invite anybody else with
you guys wherever you went.
>> Listening to Kelly talk, she
felt like an outcast.
She felt like she needed to
belong somewhere, and maybe she
really does belong with Fang.
>> I was starting to count down
the days and the hours.
>> Not much we can do, but...
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know, it's so weird.
They are just so fake.
Like, I'm a salesperson.
I know I can analyze people and,
like, get along with all
personalities.
And even change my personality,
and act like something
sometimes.
But, to them, it was just like,
I would sit there and just,
like, listen to them.
I definitely would rather jump
ship and go with Fang than I
would with old Kota.
'Cause, you know what?
They didn't even give me a
chance.
And I think Crystal and G-Sizzle
and Ken have something going on.
So, I definitely want to be a
part of that because they
overrule all the votes.
>> What you see.
(imitating): "Cool, awesome!"
"What's up? Like, cool!"
>> Oh, he's got two.
>> Oh, he pimp daddy.
>> Sweet!
>> He's pimp daddy Ace.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my God. Duh. My girl.
>> Uh, cha-ching.
>> Okay, it can be done.
>> That's money in the bank.
>> The numbers are here.
>> When I saw Kelly on that mat
and she was the last one picked,
I knew I could sway her to my
side because she did not get
along with Kota.
Oh, yeah, she's also hot.
There you go.
>> I know.
I'm so happy that I get to,
like, talk, and you guys, like,
talk back.
>> Right now, I am only using
her for a vote.
>> We got tree mail!
>> Oh, my God.
It's a lacrosse stick.
>> Oh, crap.
>> Is that a ball?
>> Yeah.
>> Aw!
>> "Practice, practice, shoot
and toss.
Like water polo meets lacrosse,
Time to show them who is boss,
You can never afford an
immunity loss."
I really am trying physically
to try my best, but, man, this
game takes a toll on a
47-year-old woman like me.
(laughs)
It just does.
>> You use your left hand and
your right.
It will go faster.
Here, somebody else can try.
>> I don't know that Randy and
Susie can really pull their
weight when it comes to the
challenges themselves.
I think it will be really hard
to put Randy out before Susie,
but it's certainly not out of
the question.
Susie is doing a great job
around camp.
And if Randy has a poor
performance on a challenge and
he's not really doing much
around camp, shoot, I would
rather keep Susie around.
The question will really be,
"How does Randy perform when it
comes time to do the
challenges?"
(all laughing)
>> Randy.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to
get to today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
GC, take back immunity.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
each have a raft and a paddle.
On my go, I'll toss a ball into
the water.
You will race to gain
possession of the ball.
Using your paddles, you will
pass the ball from one tribe
mate to another until you are
close enough that you can toss
the ball into your opponent's
goal, scoring a point for your
tribe.
First tribe to three wins
immunity, is safe in this game.
Losers go to Tribal Council
where the fourth person will be
voted out.
Make sense?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: We'll get you in the
boats.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
It takes three points to win.
Survivors ready?
Go!
These boats are not easy to
control.
Maneuvering is going to be half
the battle.
Your goal is to pass from one
tribe mate to another until you
are close enough to score.
>> That's my girl!
>> PROBST: Jacquie going to get
to the ball first for Fang.
Jacquie has it, loses it
quickly.
Jacquie struggling now to get
back to it.
Marcus taking his time, scoops
it up easily.
Ace in the goalie position.
Marcus just moving it down,
nobody even attacking Marcus.
Crystal just watching.
>> Get it, Ken!
>> PROBST: Kelly not doing
anything.
Kenny can't do anything.
Marcus passes in closer to
Randy.
Randy's got it.
Going to take a shot at the
goal, and he scores!
Just like that.
>> Take that!
Let's go! Come on!
>> PROBST: Kota on the board.
>> That's a boy, Randy!
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Kota leads, 1-zip.
Playing to three.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Matty out quickly for Fang.
>> Come on, Matty! Get to it!
>> PROBST: Marcus fighting to
get there first.
Kelly making no progress.
Ace now out of the goalie
spot using his hands.
He's now out on the course.
Marcus going to get there first
for Kota.
Marcus with a nice little pass
to himself.
Marcus like he's done this
before.
>> Kelly, get up there, too!
>> Kelly!
Kelly, the ball!
>> Come on, Kelly! Get to it!
>> Get over there, Randy.
>> Randy's open!
>> Take your time.
Take your time.
>> PROBST: Kelly not doing much.
Marcus passes down to Randy.
He's got a free goal if he can
get to it.
>> Randy, go!
>> PROBST: Nobody on the Fang
goal!
How does that happen?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Kota scores their
second point.
>> Nice, guys, nice!
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Fang could not make
that easier!
>> I can't control the boat.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Kota leads 2-zip.
It only takes three to win.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Marcus once again out quickly
for Kota.
Ace racing to get possession.
Marcus once again gets to the
ball first.
>> Nice, Ace, get to it!
>> PROBST: Trying to control it.
Loses it to Ace.
Ace having trouble getting back
to it.
Kelly just hanging back.
Marcus tosses it between
Kenny and Crystal and now
Marcus is going to pass Kenny.
>> Come on, Kenny, go!
>> PROBST: Kenny virtually
useless in this challenge.
>> Ace, yeah!
>> Atta, boys!
>> PROBST: Ace coming to get in
on this.
>> Marcus, do it!
>> Watch out. Ace is behind you.
>> PROBST: No hands!
>> Let's go, Marcus!
>> Give it to me, man.
>> PROBST: Marcus tosses to
Randy down close.
Randy's got a shot on goal.
>> Randy, go for it!
>> You've got this, Randy.
>> PROBST: This could do it.
No, just short.
>> Yeah, Matty!
>> PROBST: Dan and Matty
fighting for that ball right at
the goal.
No, Matty with a great block!
Dan, you're out of your boat.
You're not in it until you're
back in your boat.
>> Get to that corner!
>> Oh, my God!
Go, Randy!
>> PROBST: Ace knocks it out
of Randy.
Now Ace is out of his boat.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Randy scores for
Kota!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Kota wins immunity.
>> Yes, yeah!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: One of the most
lopsided challenges thus far.
Kota, congratulations.
Immunity and no Tribal Council.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Fang, without
question, one of the worst
performances I've seen at a
challenge.
I got nothing for you except
a date with me tonight at Tribal
Council where today's
performance will cost somebody
a shot at a million dollars.
That's what you have to figure
out this afternoon.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you at Tribal.
Kota, congratulations.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> (tribal chanting)
(yawning fiercely)
>> The immunity challenge was
so much fun.
It was like we were legless
chickens racing against sleek
weasels and losing badly
along the way.
>> It seemed like the plan
failed from the very start.
>> Kenny, you okay?
>> Yeah, I mean, I was...
>> Kenny, you sucked out there.
>> I'm sorry.
>> Kenny, you were stuck in the
same spot.
>> I don't understand how that
worked.
Like, 'cause I kept on turning
around in circles.
>> That was bad.
That was bad, Kenny.
>> You were pretty good,
Jacquie.
>> It's hard to play defense
in that game.
Should've, could've,
would've.
>> Over it.
>> Originally we were thinking
about voting for Ace or Jacquie
tonight, but judging by the way
that Kelly performed today,
Kelly's going home tonight is
what I'm thinking.
Um, I'm going to talk to the
others.
I'm going to talk to Kenny and
Crystal, and I'm sure everybody
will be fine with voting Kelly
out tonight.
>> So, G, what do you think?
>> I don't know.
I think, uh...
I think we should definitely
keep Ace.
He's, uh, you seen him today.
Yeah, I mean, um, but I think,
I mean, maybe we should switch
it to Kelly, man.
She kind of has a bad attitude
about stuff and she... Jacquie
did at least all right today.
Are you all cool with that?
>> I'm good with Kelly.
I'll put it out.
>> I don't want to lose no more.
>> The dangerous thing about
that is, if, if Sugar has the
immunity idol, I think she'll
be more than likely to give it
to Ace than to Jacquie.
She won't give it to Kelly.
>> That's the only flip side.
>> And who knows if she even
has it.
>> I know.
Like, voting Kelly tonight, it
would be a risk.
>> Yeah, if we vote off Kelly
tonight...
>> It would be a risk.
>> The deal was, whoever lost
the immunity challenge, ends up
picking up Sugar.
And, unfortunately, that's us.
She could have the immunity
idol and the last thing we
want is for Ace, Sugar and
Jacquie to become the power in
this tribe.
So, what's the deal?
>> No.
>> Not Kelly?
Jacquie?
>> Yeah, Jacquie.
>> Because if Sugar comes here
with the immunity idol, it'll
take...
>> She'll share it among
those three.
>> With Jacquie.
>> She was close to Jacquie
and Ace.
>> Which means they'll have
three.
>> I don't want him to have any
kind of power in our tribe,
not even three.
The closest he'll have is two.
>> Nah, tell us how you feel.
>> I think Kelly.
I think Kelly's the weakest
link.
We were gonna vote out Sue next.
What's the difference in Sue
and Kelly?
Not a damn thing.
>> The difference is, uh, Sugar
may have the immunity idol.
Ace, Sugar, and Jacquie-- those
three right now is real deadly.
>> You cool?
>> Yeah.
>> I was talking to Crystal,
GC, and Kenny.
So I go... so I go, "We can't
rid of the strong people; we
can't get rid off the strong
people; there's no way," and he
started to believe me.
And then they wanted... then
they were talking about taking
out you, and I was, like, "No,
no, no, we can't take out
Jacquie, she's too strong, she's
too strong, she's too strong,"
but they're, like, worried that
you and Ace are allied, so when
what's-her-face comes back that
you and him are gonna be
allied...
>> Matty told me that everybody
assumes that Sugar's gonna have
the idol coming back 'cause
she'll be out there for four
days now.
And they all want to vote me
out.
I'm feeling totally on the outs
right now.
I'm really, really nervous.
>> I work off my ass off in the
challenges.
>> People are scared.
>> But you guys would still
help, like...
>> No, it's not that.
It's just, like...
>> I want to be with you guys.
'Cause I'm on the outskirts of
anything, so if I try even to
join with Ace and Sugar, I know
they're not gonna bring me to
the end.
>> Jacquie seems very genuine.
After I had a talk with Jacquie,
I kind of wanted to go take out
Kelly before Jacquie.
If we make the wrong choice
right now, it will hurt really
bad later.
So my mind is not made up right
now.
I can try to vote for Kelly
tonight, but... it's not gonna
do anything.
You really need to talk to
Crystal.
>> It sucks.
So, I just... like, I was, like,
"Well, is there any way that I
could get in, like, a tight
alliance with you guys," you
know?
>> We thought you and... you and
Ace were fairly close.
>> We never had an alliance.
It would be awesome if we had,
like, a really strong united...
>> You did a... you did a hell
of a job today.
>> I worked my ass off, and I,
like, actually want to be here.
>> Yeah, you played your ass
off.
>> Thank you.
>> I was, like, "Damn."
>> I want to be here so bad...
>> Jacquie is a nervous wreck.
Jacquie was just pretty much
begging and pleading with me,
"Crystal, please keep me in the
game.
I've tried so hard.
I want to be here."
>> ...close with GC and Kenny?
>> Yeah.
>> 'Cause you guys need a
fourth.
>> Yeah, that's the thing.
>> I want to be the fourth so
bad, please... (laughs)
>> And the whole time she's
talking to me, she's-she's
welling up and she is pulling at
my heartstrings.
You know, because I'm, like,
"Damn, this girl played her ass
off today, and maybe she really
does want to be here."
>> I would be with you guys till
the end.
So anyways, I just wanted to
talk to you 'cause I didn't get
to talk to you.
And I'm, like... I'm, like,
"Kenny, I feel like...
(continues indistinctly)
>> As of right now, I don't know
what to do because I need
someone on my team that's gonna
fight... and that's gonna work
hard, you know, and that's what
she is.
>> PROBST: Welcome to another
Tribal Council starring the Fang
Tribe.
GC, it's got to be getting
old.
>> I like to see you, Jeff.
But I don't like seeing you
under these circumstances.
You know, it's good to have the
strongest team as possible.
Anytime you lose somebody, it
just hurts your team even more.
>> PROBST: Matty, is that the
criteria right now: Keep this
tribe as strong as possible?
>> Yeah, according to Matty, it
is.
And, uh, after today's
performance, I was completely
embarrassed.
So yeah, I want to keep this
tribe as strong as possible.
>> PROBST: Kenny, let's talk
about the switch.
You lose Dan, Randy, and Susie,
but you gain Jacquie, Ace, and
Kelly.
Can you trust them?
>> Um, right now, in three days,
it's really hard to trust
anybody, Jeff.
You have to build trust from the
beginning and see who they
really are, and that's how you
trust somebody.
>> PROBST: Matty, do you trust
Ace now, as a Fang member?
>> I don't know if I trust
Ace, but I want Ace on my side.
He's a powerful contributor, and
I want him on my team right now.
>> PROBST: Ace, should they
trust you guys?
>> You know, Ken's completely
right.
Until we prove ourselves, it's
hard to be, like, "Trust me,
trust me, trust me," even if
we're telling the complete
truth.
Right now you go and try and
make us as strong as possible
and just do what's best for the
tribe.
>> PROBST: Jacquie, how
frustrating is it to come from a
tribe that really had it
together, to come to this tribe,
where it's almost as if there's
something in the water?
You just... dissolve.
>> When I came to the tribe, I
thought we would have, like,
awesome teamwork.
Like, I thought we were for sure
gonna win any challenge over
Kota Tribe, and I was working
my butt off.
Like, I was hoping that we'd
win.
I definitely didn't want to be
here.
>> PROBST: Kelly, you haven't
been with this tribe very long.
Concerned at all that it's you
tonight?
>> Well, I'm definitely
concerned, but there's other
Fang members that clearly were
weak today.
>> PROBST: Who's weaker than
you?
>> Kenny was weaker than me
today, and Crystal was weaker
than me today.
>> That's just one challenge;
I'm not weaker than her.
>> Exactly. But it's just,
like... I'm just saying that,
like, I was moving in the
situation and I was, like, going
after it.
>> I didn't just sit and watch.
I tried to move that rowboat as
fast as and as best as I could,
but it wasn't moving.
So I was in the game.
I just wasn't participating as
much as I normally do.
That just wasn't my cup of tea
today.
>> PROBST: It was really clear,
the three people who
contributed.
It was Jacquie, Ace, and Matty.
Ace, if this group is truly
trying to keep its tribe
strong-- even though you're a
former Kota member-- do you feel
safe?
>> No. I'm scared.
But, like, I mean, I don't think
it would be the best strategic
move on their part to knock me
out now, just 'cause I can help,
physically, mentally as
possible.
>> PROBST: Jacquie, if the truth
is, this tribe wants to keep
this tribe strong, you are
arguably one of the strongest
people, men or women.
>> I know, but I'm so nervous.
I-I don't feel safe at all
because all of us Kota members
are in the minority.
I mean, there's only three of
us, and I just feel like I could
easily just get picked off.
>> PROBST: Kenny, if the four
Fang vote together tonight, who
should be most worried?
>> I would say Kelly or Jacquie
would have to be worried
tonight because we do need
physical players on this tribe
to start winning challenges.
So either one of them.
>> PROBST: All right, it's time
to get to the vote.
Matty, you're up.
>> (whispers): Kel, you voted
for me last time.
There's nothing like returning
the favor.
>> (whispers): Sorry.
>> It probably would have been
smarter to keep you, but this is
how it is.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: If anybody has a
hidden immunity idol and you
wanted to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
Okay. Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out'll be asked to
leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Jacquie.
Kelly. One vote Jacquie;
one vote Kelly.
Kelly. Two votes Kelly;
one vote Jacquie.
Jacquie. We're tied.
Two votes Kelly;
two votes Jacquie.
Jacquie.
That's three votes Jacquie;
two votes Kelly.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon:
Jacquie.
That's four; that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Jacquie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, one thing is for certain:
Sugar will be returning from
Exile Island and will become the
newest member of the Fang Tribe.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Stay tuned for scenes from
our next episode.
>> Next time on Survivor:
(indistinct talking)
>> (whispers): Quiet!
>> ...Mother Nature pays a
visit...
(elephant trumpeting)
...and GC goes missing...
...right before a challenge.
>> BOTH: GC!
>> So, I just got voted out of
Survivor, and I'm so upset.
I'm... I... kind of thought
coming, if I would have stayed
in more one round, I feel like I
could have made it all the way
in this game.
So they were probably smart in
saving their own butts.
But I'll be waiting for when
they get kicked off.
(chuckles)