>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
(elephant trumpets)
Kota closing in on a big win!
Throughout the game, the yellow
tribe Kota has been beating
up on the red tribe Fang.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Kota wins reward!
And some of the Kota players
have not been gracious winners.
>> Mmm!
(sniffles)
Wah, wah, wah.
>> Randy to me, he's a troll
under the bridge that's just
mean and angry with the world.
Do not disrespect me like that.
>> PROBST: On day 22, both
tribes were invited to eat
together...
>> Chow down, Kenny.
>> PROBST: ...at a feast where
Charlie robbed Kenny of a clue
to a hidden immunity idol.
>> You guys, I feel bad not
sharing this 'cause I saw the
whole thing.
So I feel like you guys should
take a look, too.
>> There is my chance to find
the hidden immunity idol for
myself, and Charlie blew it for
me.
>> PROBST: The idol was lost
when Marcus convinced everyone
to toss it away.
>> These people are so stupid.
I got ten people to throw an
immunity idol into the ocean.
>> PROBST: At the end of the
feast, the tribes were
reshuffled.
>> Congratulations, you have
just divided yourself into two
new tribes.
>> PROBST: Crystal and Kenny
were swapped from the red tribe
to the yellow tribe, where they
were outnumbered, but not
outplayed.
>> Really?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Cleverly, they
convinced Susie to help them
take out Marcus.
The tribe has spoken.
In one swift move, Kenny and
Crystal had knocked out one of
their biggest rivals.
Just when you think you're in
control of this game, blindside.
And after enduring 24 days of
grief, life is looking pretty
good for the underdogs.
Only nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Ah, Kenny, you impressed me.
All that talking you did.
I'm proud of you, though,
that you're coming out of your
shell like that.
That's great.
>> Tonight was a huge night for
me because it could have been
me tonight, and thank God it
wasn't.
I learned from Crystal at the
last seven Tribals.
(laughter)
I've been under the radar at
Fang in the beginning, and now
I have to stand up for myself.
And so far, the last two Tribal
Councils I've been to, they've
been blindsides because-because
of me.
>> Well, I bet Marcus didn't
see that coming.
>> No.
>> The next one to go is Bob.
So Bob should be worried right
now.
>> If I'm to last, I'm assuming
I need to be in a merge.
If we're not in a merge, I
think I'm history.
Even though my-- I teach
science.
Um, that was a little joke.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
(deep growling breaths)
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Good thing we're out of rice,
nothing to cook.
>> We're out here, 25th day,
and we can't even produce fire,
not even any rice to cook.
And I'm hoping for a merge
any day.
The longer I stay on this tribe,
the closer I go to going home.
(elephant trumpeting)
>> Oh, God.
>> Ooh, he's got a flag or
something.
Could it be the new tribe flag?
>> Oh, God, I can't take it
anymore.
Open the bag.
Put it down.
>> There's a note up here.
>> Charlie's gonna read it.
>> Golf, it's golf.
>> Oh, you're right.
>> It's a golf flag.
>> It is a golf flag.
Oh, my heart is palpitating.
>> "It will be fun, long drives
and short putts.
You may need more practice than
anyone thinks.
A once-in-a-lifetime cultural
trip for those who perform best
on the links."
>> There's a slingshot.
>> So we got tree mail this
morning, but I was really
hoping that it was going to be
merge, something merge-esque,
'cause I want to see Marcus
again.
Randy, I can't hold it up
much longer.
>> That's not bad.
>> That's great.
(Corinne groans)
>> The Kota alliance from the
get-go is me, Charlie and
Marcus.
As long as that's intact, I
don't really care who goes home.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Fang getting your first look at
the new Kota.
Marcus voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Huge reactions from the Fang
tribe.
Corinne, you look miserable.
>> I'm pissed, yeah.
He didn't deserve to leave the
game.
>> Then who does?
Who does deserve to leave the
game?
>> It's a game.
We all deserve it.
It's a game.
>> I know it's a game, but I'm
sad.
I think a lot of people out
here complain a lot.
Marcus never did that.
He was enjoying every second
out here.
>> I don't understand, I don't
understand why he doesn't
deserve to leave the game.
>> It's not that anyone
deserves it.
It's just that I think that, uh,
he earned his right to be here
longer, I guess.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's reward
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yes, we are.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you're going to do a
little golfing, Survivor style.
Using a large slingshot, you
will aim and shoot your ball
toward the hole...
until finally you land your
ball in the hole.
The tribe with the lowest
number of shots wins the hole.
The best two out of three wins
reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: You will be taken to
a Gabonese village, where you
will enjoy a beautiful dance
ceremony, have a nice meal...
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: ...and spend the
night.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: You'll return to camp
in the morning.
In addition, the winning tribe
will send one person from the
losing tribe to Exile Island.
Fang, you have one extra
member-- sitting somebody out.
Who you going to sit out this
time?
>> Is that cool?
Okay.
>> PROBST: All right, Corinne,
you'll be on the bench.
Everybody else, we'll get you
started.
Kota has the first shot.
300 yards to the hole, slight
downhill grade.
>> One, two, three.
>> PROBST: Bob launches back.
Just over my head.
Nice shot.
Just shy of 150 yards.
Fang is up.
Matty launches.
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Another nice shot.
Head over.
Both drives pretty even.
Fang outdrove Kota by just a
bit, so Kota will shoot first.
>> Ready?
One, two, three, go.
>> PROBST: Bob launches
straight at the hole.
And a great kick.
>> Oh, slow down.
>> It's all right-- perfect.
>> PROBST: Nice shot by Kota.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Matty back with the
second shot for Fang.
>> No.
>> PROBST: And his shot goes
way left.
But it gets a pretty good
bounce.
Ends up about 20 yards from the
hole.
We are tied.
Two shots each.
Fang with their third shot.
Randy, way short.
Third shot for Kota.
Kenny's going to be the shooter
this time.
Could win the hole right here.
And he does it.
Kota scores the first point!
Moving on to the next hole.
Second hole.
225 yards, uphill.
>> One, two, three.
>> PROBST: Nice shot.
Just past the 125-yard marker.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Matty back shooting
now for Fang.
Nice shot from Fang.
Both balls very close.
Come on down.
Fang, you're furthest out.
You'll shoot first.
He lets it go.
Hits high on the mountain,
falls all the way down, just
six inches from the hole.
>> Whoo!
>> Nice, nice.
>> PROBST: Kota with their
second shot; got to get close.
Bob with a decent shot but
still about 30 feet away from
the hole.
>> That's all right.
We'll get it in.
>> PROBST: Kota with their
third shot.
Probably need to get this one
in the hole.
Kenny gives it a good shot, but
it's too long.
>> It's all right.
It's all right, Kenny.
>> PROBST: Fang now with their
third shot.
Fang needs this to stay alive.
>> Like that?
Go widen out, Charlie, widen
out.
>> Just not too much power.
>> Widen out.
>> That's it.
>> PROBST: And he does it.
Fang ties it up, 1-1.
This is it.
Final hole.
200 yards, uphill.
We are tied, one each.
Playing to two.
Matty launches one.
Gets a nice kick.
Dead center perfect.
Kota's up.
Bob launches.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: A huge drive.
Nice off the tee box for Kota.
Kota!
>> It's not about deuces.
>> PROBST: Matty, back.
Launches a nice one.
>> It's all right.
It's all right.
Come on, roll.
>> PROBST: Look at that, kicking
all the way back.
Decent shot by Fang, in good
shape.
Kota, you're up.
>> One, two, three.
>> PROBST: Bob launches.
Far to the right, but he's
getting a good kick.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Kota in pretty
decent shape.
Kota now up with their third
shot.
Winner of this hole wins reward.
Kenny just misses.
Six inches too far, rolls down
the hill, opens the door for
Fang.
He had to go short, and puts it
right on the edge of the hole.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Big-time pressure on
Kota for this shot.
Kota, with their fourth shot,
knowing that Fang is literally
on the edge of the hole.
Kenny just overshoots it.
Matty can win it for Fang right
here.
>> Could.
>> Charlie, hold it out here.
>> Okay.
>> No rush, no rush.
>> Just drop it way out here,
Charlie.
>> Farther, farther.
Matty, don't pull it back.
Just set it forward...
>> Shh!
>> Please.
>> Calm down, calm down.
>> Go forward.
Pull it forward more, Charlie.
>> PROBST: A lot of discussion.
They're right on the hole.
How can they blow it?
>> Tension, Randy!
Okay, hold on.
Stop.
We got to...
>> Can I do it?
>> No, I got it.
No, you can't do it.
>> Matty, please.
>> Simmer down, Randy.
>> Just drop it.
No pitching on the court at all.
Right now, just drop it!
>> Shh!
>> Randy, Randy...
We all need to...
If we win this, I want to win
this happy and calm.
>> Please.
>> I got it, man.
>> There should be no pitch on
it.
>> I know, buddy.
>> Then drop it!
Let's go home!
>> Randy, we want to go home
happy.
>> Here we go.
>> Charlie.
>> PROBST: Fang one big happy
tribe, obviously.
Fang with the win for reward.
This should be a fun afternoon.
>> We're hungry and tense.
>> Yes!
>> Corinne, we won!
>> Good job.
Good job, Bob.
>> Why are you mad?
>> There's no need to spring
it, man!
>> I know, but I just...
>> Randy!
Whatever, we won.
Chill out!
>> We did good, bud.
>> Good Lord!
>> PROBST: Fang,
congratulations.
You must now choose one person
from the Kota tribe to send to
Exile Island.
>> We figure we're going to
send Bob.
>> PROBST: Corinne, why Bob?
>> I just know that he can find
the idol, and I wish him the
best of luck in doing that.
>> PROBST: Bob, grab your stuff.
Here's a map.
Have fun.
>> Which way do I want to go?
>> PROBST: Straight up there.
Bob will return in time for the
next immunity challenge.
>> Bob's never going to find
that idol because nobody has
that idol but me, and no matter
who gets sent to Exile, the
only three people that know are
Matty, Kenny, and Crystal.
>> PROBST: All right, Fang, you
will leave from here, be taken
straight to your hard-earned
reward.
Grab your stuff.
Head out.
>> That was the most
anxiety-ridden challenge I've
had in this whole competition.
I felt like I was going to
have, like, four heart attacks.
>> Matty, I don't know what got
into the guy, but what he
pulled was ugly.
He would not even listen.
It was like The Outer Limits.
♪ ♪
(cheering)
>> Arriving to this African
village was a surreal feeling.
(singing)
I am the only Fang member that
has been trapped at Fang the
entire game, and, uh, to finally
get a reward, the man upstairs
is looking out, man, because I
needed it.
(chanting)
(singing)
>> All we're thinking is
food, but instead, they start
beating us with leaves that
are covered in water and, like,
stripping our clothes off of us
to wash us down.
Like, you felt like a human
being again.
It was nice.
It was really nice.
And then we went to the next
tribal ceremony and this little
girl-- she was very, very cute.
She was, like, too small to,
like, follow everybody, and,
like, hang out so I paid some
attention to her and then she
was, like, glued to me.
Which was cute, um, but I'd be
the last person anyone would
think would, like, chum up to a
two-year-old.
>> I was stoked when I saw
Marcus gone.
>> I was shocked.
>> 'Cause you were just thinking
about the reward.
>> Well, yeah, we probably would
have lost if Marcus was there,
probably.
>> It's crazy how that happened.
Ace, Stan, Marcus, boom, boom,
boom.
The three power players.
>> Yeah.
>> Marcus getting voted out is,
like, the lowest moment I've
had in this game, because Marcus
and I had been playing together
since the first day, like, not
just as, like, strategists in
this game, but as, like, really
good friends.
And now with him gone it's like
ugh, who do we turn to, because
he did a lot of thinking for us.
♪ ♪
>> The dancers were great.
I kind of got the feeling one of
them liked me.
I haven't had a girl come on to
me in about 20 years, but I
think, uh... I think one of them
kind of liked me.
I hate to dance.
My feet hurt.
My knee hurts.
My shoulder hurts.
And just ate about four pounds
of food, but, hell, I danced
with her.
♪ ♪
>> I don't know what came into
me, but I was just feeling it
and going for it.
It was, like, the two cultures
colliding with their styles of
dance.
It was so cool.
I think that I will be voted out
next, so I'm really nervous.
But my main objective was to
allow myself a break from the
game of Survivor, and, uh, it
gave me some relief that I
needed desperately.
♪ ♪
>> Huh.
No, don't get stuck again.
♪ ♪
All I'm doing is going around in
circles, like an idiot.
It's like one of the worst
feelings ever.
Wait, I know what to do.
(grunts)
I'm not an outdoors type of guy.
At home I usually sit in the
room playing video games most
of the time.
Uh-huh.
But right now, I'm feeling that
I... I'm getting to know how to
play this game more,
this game of Survivor.
Three fishes.
Three tilapias.
Oh, ladies!
Fried fish.
>> Awesome!
>> That is so cool, Kenny boy!
>> Bob's at Exile Island, so,
therefore, I'm the only man at
Kota with two very beautiful
women.
>> Thank you, Ken.
>> You did awesome!
>> Who would've thought the
little guy in this game would
be the provider for them.
>> This is good!
>> The best fish I've had out
here.
To me that's a Gabon feast for
me.
I am very proud of myself for
what I've done so far in this
game, and if people want to
take me out, I will take them
out before they take me out,
any way I can.
So, right now, I know for a fact
that I can win this game.
♪ ♪
>> "Across the lake you see so
well, there lies a sandy
crater."
Well, I think I'll go for clue
two.
I just arrived at Exile and my
choice is not to take comfort.
I'm going to go for the clue and
that's a real clear choice for
me because I am, uh, in deep
doo-doo back at camp.
Sandy crater.
Wow.
"Now turn around, go back to the
lake.
On one tree hill, time for
salvation's sake."
"Walk along a yonder creek.
Beneath the burnt wood is the
thing you seek."
Huh.
"Through creatures unknown,
you'll have to wade, the
deliverance shall be made."
But I don't see it.
The first three clues came boom,
boom, boom.
And this one has got me
completely perplexed.
I can't think of a leaf that
I've left unturned.
I have been more than
frustrated.
Maybe Sugar found the idol.
I'm not exactly sure, but I've
got to do something.
My plan is to make something
that looks like an idol.
I found something that looked
like a skull, so I took the
resin that I found in one of
the trees and glued the front
of it with resin, and then taken
knick-knacks that I found
around.
This is my new fake idol.
I potentially have an idol
that could threaten somebody
else in the tribe.
It's sort of like when you're
holding up a bank; you don't
necessarily need the gun.
If they think you got a gun,
they might leave you alone.
>> We got mail!
>> "Today, it's not important
if you're fast or stronger or
smarter.
To avoid going home tonight,
be the best fire starter."
>> It's individual, it sounds
like.
>> Oh, God, I hope not.
>> We don't know! Shush up!
>> It said build a fire?
>> No, Crystal... there's no way
Crystal is gonna start a fire.
There's no way Susie's gonna
be able to start a fire.
There's no way Kenny is.
>> They could give Crystal a
book of matches and gasoline,
and she can't start a fire.
We don't know if it's gonna be
tribe versus tribe or whether
it's gonna be individual
immunity, but there's a merge.
And I see Crystal again, I'll
puke.
I mean, can you imagine the
drama if the merge happens and
I was forced to stay with
Sasquatch, and you know...
>> Sasquatch is Bigfoot, which
is Crystal.
>> Okay.
>> Which is also T-Rex.
I hated Crystal from the
beginning.
Everybody knows that.
She made her bed back in the old
Fang, and I still hold a major
grudge.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Bob
returning from Exile Island.
First things first, Matty, we'll
take back the immunity idol.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
Today, tribal immunity is not
what you seek.
Individual immunity is what you
are playing for...
because you are no longer two
tribes.
Drop your buffs.
You are merged.
(Sugar squeals)
>> Yes! Awesome!
>> Whoa!
>> The merge is a new lease on
life for me.
I knew my days were numbered.
I'm the luckiest guy in Gabon.
>> Are you okay?
>> Yeah, I missed you so much.
My buddy!
>> PROBST: Matty, here are your
buffs.
Pass them out. Put 'em on.
>> Oh, my God, it's so clean.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to your challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: It is only fitting,
as you now enter the individual
portion of this game, that the
first challenge should test how
well you would do on your own.
Today you will make fire.
You will each have a flint and
steel and a box of fire-making
supplies.
Your goal: make a fire high
enough to burn through your
rope.
First person to burn through
their rope wins immunity and
guaranteed a one-in-eight shot
at a million bucks.
(whistles)
Losers, Tribal Council, where
somebody will be voted out and
become the second member of our
jury.
High enough stakes?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: All right, we'll draw
for positions.
We'll get started.
Okay, you each have a flint and
steel.
You got fire-making supplies.
Everything you've had at camp
from day one.
This is for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Let's see what you've learned
in your 27 days in Gabon, West
Africa.
This is fundamental to being
able to survive on your own.
And you are on your own in this
game now.
Randy trying to get a spark.
Bob really trying to get
something sparking down there.
Susie looking for a spark.
Randy just starting over.
(blowing)
>> Come on, baby.
Come on, come on.
>> PROBST: Susie first to get
flame.
>> Come on, baby, come on.
>> PROBST: Using that husk to
get it burning.
Now she's got to get something
that she can keep going.
Matty with a little injury,
making no progress at all.
Susie working hard to build a
little teepee.
>> Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Sugar has flame.
Trying to turn it into a fire
that will sustain itself, start
to grow.
Sugar and Susie both with fire.
Somebody else better get in this
challenge.
(groans)
Sugar coming on strong now.
>> Come on.
>> So close.
>> PROBST: Susie's fire
continues to grow.
Nobody else is even in it.
>> This sucks!
>> PROBST: Sugar with a very
impressive fire.
If somebody doesn't hurry up,
Sugar and Susie are going to be
tough to beat.
>> There we go. There we go.
>> PROBST: They're neck and
neck.
>> Come on, come on, come on.
>> PROBST: Susie getting very
close now.
Sugar looking very good.
>> There we go.
Now let's get some flames on
the... come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Susie's fire is
starting to burn high enough
now to burn through that rope.
Sugar's fire is up to the rope.
Both in good position.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Susie wins immunity!
>> I can't believe it!
>> Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
Susie is safe tonight at Tribal
Council.
(applause)
Guaranteed a one-in-eight shot
at a million dollars.
For the rest of you, one of you
going home tonight.
You will now return to one camp
together.
You will be going back to what
was formally Fang.
It is now a new camp.
You will have everything you
need there to give yourself a
new tribe name, build a new
tribe flag.
Any personal items, any reward
items left back at the old Kota
camp will be waiting there for
you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you at Tribal.
Congratulations.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> Finally, we merged, just
everybody together, nine of us.
But I hated Fang from the
beginning.
There's no way I'm going back
to camp tonight with Crystal.
She'll be gone or I'll be gone.
(trumpeting)
>> Good to be here.
>> Welcome back.
Congratulations, everyone.
I can't believe we've got
canned food here.
That must be our beans.
>> I think it's rice.
>> Oh, good!
>> Beans or beanie weenie.
>> Yeah, let's eat it.
>> The merge totally changed the
game.
We got back, everybody paid
homage to all our new gifts.
There was rice; there was
canned food; there was beans.
There was Gabon pears.
There's coffee.
But, uh, as soon as that little
brief gratitude session was
up...
>> Want to go to the woods?
>> ...people bounced into the
jungle and started their
strategies, you know.
(exhales sharply)
>> Crystal's the way to go,
and I'm voting for Crystal.
Don't worry.
Bob will vote Crystal.
>> Yeah, the four of us are on
board for Crystal, so we just
need Sugar.
I feel very confident that
Corinne, Bob, Randy, and I are
a solid four, and I feel
confident that Matty, Kenny,
Susie, and Crystal are a solid
four.
Then, there's Sugar.
>> ♪ Hallelujah. ♪
>> And she is hanging somewhere
in the middle, and she has ties
to both sides.
But Sugar has a mind of her
own and is playing this game
very differently than all of us.
(squeals)
>> Are we on board?
>> Yeah, I'm...
I can't live with him anymore,
and he's going to cause big
problems.
>> We can do Randy next.
>> That's what I was saying.
I mean, I want you to be
comfortable, so I care about
your opinion.
My whole plan is just to stay
on Sugar because she... she is
the swing vote.
Not only do I have to act
interested in what Sugar is
saying, but I have to act like I
care about her.
>> Honestly, will you trust me?
Like, it's the best move.
>> I just know Randy is in a bad
spot and he has to stick with
us, and I just want to stay in
the game.
>> It's the Kota foursome to
the end.
>> Sugar is so weak and naive
and gullible.
I have been nasty to her for 25
days.
I was nice to her one day, and
she's sold.
So it doesn't even make sense,
but she buys it because she's
such a moron.
(trumpets)
>> Now, listen, listen, Charlie
and Corinne are the alliance.
>> They never, ever, ever break.
>> So we need to break them.
>> No, I'm going to tell you
right now.
Me and... we home, we home.
This is some real... this is the
realness over here.
>> Randy is with Kota, too.
>> Okay, if he's Kota, then
you're on their chopping list.
>> Why?
>> 'Cause Randy.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> No, but listen...
>> But they... them two got's to
be broken up.
>> Which one?
>> Corinne and Charlie.
>> Oh, they both need to go.
Corinne can go first.
>> See, Corinne is just hurting
herself with her own
personality.
>> Oh, God, she's horrendous!
I can't handle her.
She is awful, dude.
>> (laughing): I know.
>> No, really.
>> Yeah, what about...?
>> I have a personal grudge
against Charlie.
At that feast, freaking Charlie
took that paper and he made me
share it with everybody.
I could have gotten the hidden
immunity idol, and nobody would
have known, but no.
So I made up this little lie.
I said, "Charlie, he's behind
the scenes of Kota.
He's telling people what to do."
But really, no, I made it up,
and everybody listened to me.
>> Write down Charlie.
Write down Charlie, Charlie.
>> Charlie.
>> Charlie, Charlie, Charlie.
>> I'll trade that idol for his
life.
Serves him right.
We got to blindside Charlie
first.
I'm like a little rat.
I go... you know, in the corner,
and nobody knows that.
You mess with me, then you're
gone in this game.
Charlie is the brains behind the
whole Kota cabana.
>> Really, it's not...?
>> It's not Randy and not
Corinne.
We will get rid of them as soon
as we can, but Charlie tells
them what to do and he's the
brains behind it.
Yes, but he seems nice, but he
goes out and talks and whispers
to them, and then they... they
be themselves.
>> Okay.
>> So once we get rid of
Charlie, we can get rid of
Randy, Corinne, whoever you
want.
>> I think I'm the lady of the
hour because everybody is
telling me who to vote for and
chomping at the bit to, like,
get my vote for somebody.
Just "You got to vote with us.
Get the numbers, blah, blah,
blah."
So we have to come up with a
tribe name?
>> N-O-B-A-G.
>> I like that.
Gabon backwards.
>> The thing is, I don't trust
Kenny.
He lied to me about Ace.
So he could be some evil
mastermind.
And I don't trust Crystal at
all.
I certainly don't have any
allegiance to Randy and Corinne.
So I guess I don't trust any of
these guys.
>> Are we good?
>> Sure.
>> Wait-- yeah, yeah, wherever.
>> I think that's good.
>> Even though we're one tribe,
there is definitely two sides to
this tribe, and both sides of
this blue tribe want my vote for
another person, so I have no
clue what to do, but I don't owe
anything to anybody at all.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Now I'll bring in the
first member of our jury.
Marcus, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
So I'll remind you guys, from
this point forward, no talking
to the jury.
They're here to observe.
That's it.
The game is slowly shifting into
their hands.
All right, let's start at the
reward challenge.
Randy, you guys are right on the
verge of winning this challenge.
All you have to do, literally,
is just pick up the ball and
drop it in.
Where was all that tension
coming from when you're on the
verge of a win?
>> Uh, the shot that Matty took,
he would make nine times out of
ten.
If everybody would have shut up
and listened to what I was
saying, I had a shot that would
have made it ten times out of
ten.
Nobody would listen, and it was
frustrating.
>> PROBST: Charlie, you were
seeing that the tribe was
starting to break down and maybe
on the verge of blowing an easy
win.
>> Yeah, I was screaming over
both of them, "Calm down. Calm
down. Let's communicate" because
to express your point of view,
you need to communicate it, and
I think the communication really
broke down, so I hope we learned
from it.
>> PROBST: Randy, you started
off on Fang tribe, you went over
to Kota, and from that point
forward what I've seen has been,
"Don't miss 'em.
Didn't like 'em anyway."
>> Well, since we're putting
stuff out on the table, why, why
have you got issues with me?
>> Why?
>> Why do you have issues with
Crystal?
Yes, I would like to know.
If I have a problem with
anybody, it's clear.
It's not any gray area.
This is where Crystal stands.
>> Okay, w-why...?
>> W-W-Wait, I let you finish.
Let me finish.
>> I never even started.
How can you let me finish?
>> You're opening up your mouth.
Let me finish.
Now, what is it that I did to
Randy for Randy to be bashing
Crystal so much at Kota camp?
>> Okay, you want a list?
>> What'd I do to Randy, really?
>> All right.
The first nine days of this
game...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...you made Fang a living
hell, you and your boy GC.
>> Okay...
>> You guys were running...
Hey, I let you talk.
You going to let me talk or
what?
>> Speak on.
>> All right.
You and your posse ran the tribe
like it was a gang.
When you guys had power, you
guys were arrogant; you were
hard to get along with.
You were causing the division in
our tribe and were the reason
that we lost all those times.
>> All right, okay.
>> Y-You, you want more?
>> You feel like you have to say
some more, we ain't got nothing
but time.
>> PROBST: Crystal, you've been
pretty vocal, sharing what's on
your mind at times.
Ever regret any of your emotions
out here?
>> No, I don't.
Yeah, I've cried when I've won.
I've cried when I lost.
I've been called delusional.
But you can guarantee one thing:
this is Crystal.
What you see is what you get,
and if you want the truth, this
is Crystal.
>> PROBST: Charlie, would you be
a little concerned if you were
Randy or Crystal, people who
have been the most vocal tonight
firing arrows back and forth?
>> I think that if you're just
saying something just for your
own selfish reasons to get it
off your chest, that doesn't
make sense.
I definitely think you need to
process what comes out of your
mouth, especially in this unique
circumstance.
>> PROBST: Kenny, the nine of
you, who have been battling for
so long, now come together.
Do opinions start to change?
>> Well, like, with Charlie, for
instance, I didn't know too much
about Charlie, and I like
Charlie.
Just talking with him, I know
that he's a nice guy.
>> PROBST: Charlie, has your
opinion of Kenny changed now
that you've spent some time with
him?
>> Not at all.
I thought Kenny was a great guy
when I met him, so my opinion
has stayed the same and I've
continued to develop a
friendship with Kenny.
>> PROBST: Randy, is there
anybody that changed for you?
>> Yeah, Kenny, he's, he's, he's
not a little kid anymore.
He's definitely grown up and
that's not the Kenny I saw weeks
ago.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about your
time out here, Sugar.
Can it actually be an advantage
to have spent so many times away
from the game on Exile because
you didn't have the same
opportunity to irritate people
that Randy did and Crystal did?
>> Um, being away from everybody
just gives them a chance to talk
about me more.
I would not annoy everybody.
I don't hurt people's feelings
and I don't talk crap about
people behind their backs and I
have a good idea of who
everybody is.
>> PROBST: All right, Susie, you
have individual immunity unless
you want to assign that to
someone else.
>> Let me think about that.
(laughter)
Nope, I'm gonna keep it.
>> PROBST: All right, you cannot
vote for Susie.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Randy, you're up.
>> (whispering): Bitch.
>> (whispering): Sorry, Charlie.
>> (whispering): You took out my
Marcus, and that makes me really
mad.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Crystal.
Who cast this vote?
>> Uh, C.C., Crystal Cox.
>> PROBST: If you don't want
somebody to know who you voted
for, you got to write a name
down.
Otherwise I have to ask.
That's two votes Crystal.
Crystal.
Three votes Crystal.
Four votes Crystal.
Charlie.
Four votes Crystal;
one vote Charlie.
Charlie.
Four votes Crystal;
two votes Charlie.
Charlie.
That's four votes Crystal;
three votes Charlie.
Charlie.
Four votes Crystal;
four votes Charlie.
One vote left.
Tenth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon and the second
member of our jury: Charlie.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good job, guys.
>> PROBST: Charlie, the tribe
has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Have fun.
>> PROBST: One thing tonight's
Tribal Council made clear to me
is that the merge has had an
impact on this game, and it
should make for a crazy finish.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
>> I'm gonna burn this house
down.
>> PROBST: Randy stirs up the
camp.
>> He is wreaking havoc.
>> I think he's crazy.
>> You're on the outs.
The final three in this game is
Kenny, Susie, and Crystal.
You're not part of it.
>> We have to get this right.
If we get this right,
the whole game will change.
>> PROBST: But Kenny will not be
denied.
>> Okay, this is a disaster.
I 100% did not see this coming.
But what can you do at this
point?
And I didn't think I would make
it past the first Tribal, so to
make it this far is amazing.
If I'm going to leave Survivor,
I'm glad it's a blindside.
Thank God Marcus is in the jury
house.
That is my saving grace.