>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
For the past 18 days, the yellow
tribe, Kota, was the king of the
jungle, winning eight out of ten
challenges.
Kota, once again, immunity is
yours.
The entire tribe was united,
except for Dan and Susie.
>> I don't have the confidence
that we get to the merge and
these people have got my back.
>> PROBST: Throughout the game,
the red tribe, Fang,
consistently made questionable
moves.
>> I'm stuck in a tribe that has
no skills.
>> PROBST: Ace made a heads-up
play...
>> That's the deal.
>> Deal?
>> Deal.
>> PROBST: ...when he pulled
Matty into an alliance with his
long-time ally, Sugar.
>> I've been relying on Ace the
whole time.
>> One of Sugar's biggest
plusses is the fact that she has
the immunity idol.
And I've got Sugar in my pocket.
>> PROBST: Their first move was
to vote out Ace's biggest enemy,
Kelly.
Kelly, the tribe has spoken.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
♪ ♪
(animals chirping, chittering)
(animal squawks in distance)
>> This is a tough game.
We're starving.
>> There's nothing to eat.
I'm starting to lose my spirit,
I'm starting to lose my hope.
It's-it's become hopeless.
I'm hopeless about Fang.
>> What happened?
>> As soon as I got up, it
tipped over.
But just a little bit came out.
But I'll scoop it back in there,
'cause it... it was just a
little bit.
>> That's a ton.
Rice is more valuable than gold,
and she just clumsily trips over
it and spills it.
I wanted to just lay into her
and chew her out, but I... it's
just pointless.
You can't cry over spilled
milk, you know?
It's just too late.
Is it done?
>> Yeah. Not so bad.
>> You guys ready?
>> Nothing like some fresh
oatmeal rice.
>> I don't want to take away
from you and Matty.
>> Crystal, eat.
>> Ace, you eat.
>> Come on, please?
>> You don't have to beg me.
You eat.
I don't want to feel like I took
away from anybody in this tribe.
So by all means, eat your full,
like you normally do.
>> This tribe, Fang tribe, we're
not working together.
Everybody has grudges against
each other.
Matty and Ace are basically
going against Crystal.
These guys are trying to call
the shots, and I don't like
that, I don't like that at all.
>> You guys don't have to say
anything, but your faces say a
thousand words.
That's the difference between me
and you guys.
>> Crystal did me a favor.
She will be the next lamb to the
slaughter.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
(animal bellows)
>> My parents are, like,
"Corinne, try not to curse so
much when you're there, because
people are gonna think you're
trashy."
(laughter)
>> I think Charlie and Marcus
and Corinne seem very, very
tight, and at times almost
exclusive.
And I'm just the type of person
that I'm always gonna feel a
little bit vulnerable, a little
bit insecure.
I mean, I wanted to clarify that
I'm, like, a really sensitive
person.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's weird when I'm not
part of a group.
I kind of, like... it-it, like,
makes me feel bad a little bit.
That's just me, like, that's how
I am with groups.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You know, I like to be part
of the group.
>> I would say that Dan is
socially inept in a lot of ways.
I don't know if he's a former
fatty or why he wasn't liked as
a child, but deep down inside
he's a little kid that's seeking
approval.
>> It's different than Fang,
where I alienated myself because
I didn't like those people.
With you guys, it's completely
opposite.
It's, like, all right, I really
like these three...
>> Dan is the ultimate paranoid
human being.
At some point, Dan is gonna be a
huge liability, and
unfortunately, there's nothing I
can do to-to sort of save him
from-from himself at this point.
>> Do you feel better?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> Okay.
>> Do you guys?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Good.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Kota getting your first look at
the new Fang Tribe.
Kelly voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> OTHERS: Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, gonna play a little
game of keep-away.
On my "go," three members of
each tribe will toss a breakable
ball back and forth, while one
member of the other tribe
attempts to smash that ball or
force it to the ground.
You'll be playing at the same
time, in two rings.
The tribe whose attacker breaks
their opponent's ball first wins
a point.
We are playing to three.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yeah.
>> Hell, yeah.
>> PROBST: The winning tribe
will be picked up by helicopter,
flown to a beautiful location
here in Gabon.
You'll be bringing with you
everything you need for a nice
afternoon picnic.
(gasps)
>> Beer.
>> Beers.
>> PROBST: You have some bread,
veggies, meats, cheeses...
>> Cheese!
>> PROBST: ...some nice drinks.
It should be a fun afternoon.
In addition, the winning tribe
will send one member of the
losing tribe to Exile Island.
Worth playing for?
>> OTHERS: Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> PROBST: Kota, you have two
extra members.
Who's gonna sit this one out?
Charlie and I would like to be
the cheerleaders today.
>> PROBST: Corinne, Charlie,
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize, we'll get
started.
First round, Randy, the attacker
for Kota, will be going up
against Fang.
Ace, the attacker for Fang,
he'll be going up against Kota.
Fang looking to break a
five-challenge losing streak.
Survivors, ready...
Go!
Ace goes after Bob in the Kota
ring.
Randy very aggressive in the
Fang ring.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Ball hits the ground.
Kota scores first point!
(cheering)
>> Yeah, Kota!
>> Over.
>> PROBST: Kota leads: one-zip.
Next round, Bob, the attacker
for Kota, Sugar, the attacker
for Fang.
>> (growls)
>> This guy is so ugly over
here.
He's such an ugly person.
He's mean.
>> PROBST: This should be fun.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Survivors, ready...
Go!
Sugar being aggressive, giving
everything she has trying to
score for Fang.
Bob takes Kenny out, doesn't
help.
Fang's still alive.
Bob takes a hard fall.
Stay after him, Sugar.
Be a hero.
>> (laughs): Okay.
>> PROBST: Fang needs to score.
Sugar, you need to pick it up.
Do not drop that ball.
>> (grunts)
>> PROBST: Big takedown from
Bob!
It doesn't work, though-- Ace
keeps the ball alive.
>> Nice, Ace!
>> PROBST: Sugar doing
nothing, absolutely nothing.
>> Come on, Sugar!
>> PROBST: Sugar's gonna have to
get aggressive, try to make
something happen.
Bob almost deflects it!
No! Another takedown by Bob on
Matty!
>> (laughing)
>> Come on, Sugar!
>> PROBST: Ace tries to get it
past Bob, but Bob shuts him
down!
Kota scores again!
Kota leads: two-zip.
We are playing to three.
This could be it.
Next round, attacking for Kota
is Dan.
He could end this challenge.
Attacking for Fang is Matty,
trying to keep Fang alive for a
big reward.
Survivors, ready...
Go!
Matty comes out strong, chasing
after that ball quickly.
Dan very aggressive on Ace.
Ace gets rid of it to Crystal.
Crystal to Sugar, back to Ace.
Ace back to Sugar. No!
Dan causes the ball to break!
Kota scores!
Kota wins reward!
(excited chatter)
All right, Kota, big decision.
You're sending one member of
Fang to Exile Island.
>> Let's go ahead and send
Sugar.
>> PROBST: Sugar, this is
unprecedented.
I don't think we've ever had
anybody be sent to Exile five
times, back-to-back-to-back...
to-back-to-back.
>> Yeah, I'm here to break
records, you know. (laughs)
>> PROBST: All right, Sugar, get
your stuff.
>> Sugar is a pinup model.
She is completely worthless when
it comes to challenges.
So when it comes to Sugar in
this game... I would really,
really, really desire her to go.
>> PROBST: Kota, it should be a
fun afternoon.
(indistinct chatter)
Fang, I got nothing for you.
>> We lost the biggest reward
yet.
It's hard, you know, when you
see them walking away.
They have everything, and we
have nothing.
And we see Kota in their
beautiful chopper just lavishing
in their reward, you know?
It's madness, it's total
madness.
♪ ♪
>> Reward was a helicopter ride,
and I was lucky enough to have
the front-row seat.
Just seeing that incredible
crater, it made my trip to
Africa.
The only thing that was beating
faster than the rotors on that
helicopter was the beating of my
heart.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Close as I want to get.
>> Holy cow.
>> Stay away from the edge.
>> You're making me nervous,
Marcus.
The beautiful scenery, it was
awesome.
It's something I thought I would
never experience, so it just
gives you more incentive, more
power, more strength to know
that you can get through this,
no matter what.
So it was very... it was very
surreal for me.
It was just amazing.
>> Let's get our blanket out.
>> This is great, let's get our
blanket out.
>> Sardines! Ha-ha!
>> I don't think in
my entire 29 years of living
I've ever been so embarrassed.
I'm humiliated. I felt pathetic.
My spirits are dropping so fast.
I look over, and, like, Sugar,
she's just, she can't do
anything.
She's just being dominated.
It was pointless for us to even
keep going.
She was just standing there
getting walked all over.
I hate it.
I'm starting to get pissed.
As long as there's physical
challenges, we're gonna lose.
Want to take a boat ride, Ace?
>> Sure, bro.
>> We need to take out Sugar.
Okay, this is what we do.
We go Kenny, Crystal and I vote
for Sugar.
You don't have to vote for
Sugar, so you're not
backstabbing her, okay?
Sugar's gone, and it's you and I
to the merge a hundred percent.
There's no question.
>> You know we're a hundred
percent, you and me.
>> No, I don't know that.
We're aligned.
Me and you are aligned, so make
me comfortable.
We need to take out Sugar or at
least get the idol out.
>> Yeah, I see the logic, dude.
I see that logic.
>> Okay, we know exactly where
it's sitting, and we can use it
to our advantage when we have
to.
>> You know what they're
talking about, right, Cri?
>> Yeah, those two asses out
there in the boat trying to get
me off.
>> They are. Will you trust me?
>> I've been there with you
from day one, Kenny.
>> We have to blindside Ace.
>> Yeah.
>> I have to talk to Sugar.
Crystal, you trust me a
hundred percent, right?
>> I trust you a hundred
percent.
>> Okay.
>> I can feel Ace, right now,
strategically, wants to get rid
of me.
The way that he's manipulating
Matty, he's a devil.
And he has to go.
>> This is... this is awesome.
>> Getting this is just
incomparable.
>> And the best part about this
is they don't get it.
>> And they may be completely
out of rice, to add insult to
injury.
>> Oh, oh...
>> What is this?
>> Oh, my...
>> Oh, my God!
>> Wait, stop. Everyone, shh!
>> Holy cow, these are letters
from home.
>> Oh, my God, they're letters!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
(gasps)
Oh, my God!
They're really letters!
>> (sobbing)
>> Bob, are you okay, man?
>> No, I'm not!
>> Your family loves you, Bob.
>> I know it. (sobbing)
(grunts)
I don't know which one to read
first.
This is from David.
>> My dad, he never writes
anything, and he wrote me a
letter.
>> Isn't that cool?
>> He never writes anything.
He wasn't even excited.
He didn't show any excitement
when I was leaving.
Wow.
>> "You should receive..."
I can't read it.
My eyes keep blurring.
I'm close to these people here,
but these are the people that
are the closest to my heart.
Life is good.
And I realize how lucky a man I
am.
I'm here.
And I can't...
I can't wait to get home to
them.
Life doesn't get better than
this.
>> Back to the Sugar Shack
for me.
I don't really know what the
hell's happening in this game.
I'm just...
trying to survive. (laughs)
Thank God for Ace.
What's funny is I'm pretty sure
we're using each other, but I
feel like my tribe thinks I'm
naive and that I'm sticking
with him out of stupidity, but
I'm sticking with him because
he's the strongest player at
this point.
So I just hope that they're not
all screwing me around.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Sugar,
returning from Exile Island.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Dan, I will take it back.
Thank you.
Good news and bad news about
today's challenge.
Bad news is, both tribes are
going to Tribal Council tonight.
Both tribes are gonna vote
somebody out.
The good news, each of you will
have an equal shot at winning...
individual immunity.
It's a log roll.
You're gonna match up
against another tribe member.
It might be somebody from the
other tribe.
It might be somebody from your
own tribe.
Your goal is to stay on the log
longer than the other person.
First person to hit the water
is out.
Winners move on.
Last person left standing wins
immunity and is safe at
tonight's Tribal Council.
>> I think I may have a target
on my back, so it's very, very
important for me personally to
go in there and win, and not
just win by a little.
Win by a lot.
>> PROBST: In addition, there is
a twist which will be revealed
after the challenge is over.
>> Another twist?
>> PROBST: We'll draw numbers,
get our matchups, we'll get
started.
All right, first matchup, Dan
taking on Ace.
All right, here we go.
Put a foot on the log.
Three, two, one, walk.
We are on. First matchup.
Good footwork.
Dan is in the water.
Ace moves on to the next round!
Next round, Charlie versus
Crystal.
This challenge is on.
Charlie and Crystal looking to
move on.
Crystal in the water first.
Charlie moving on to the next
round.
Big matchup, Marcus versus
Matty.
Good save by Marcus.
Matty's in the water.
Marcus moving on to the next
round!
Randy taking on Susie.
Both from the Kota tribe.
Nice footwork.
Ah! Susie in the water first.
Randy moving on to the next
round.
Kenny versus Sugar.
Two Fang members.
>> This dumb thing. (laughs)
>> I can't even move this.
>> PROBST: Can he fight to hang
on?
No! Kenny in the water first.
Sugar moving on.
Last of the first rounds, Bob
and Corinne.
>> Of course he did.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Who knew that would
come in handy?
Here we go, Bob versus Corinne.
Bob, the former log roll winner.
Three, two, one, walk.
(Bob whistling, Sugar laughing)
Corinne in the water first.
Bob moving on!
All right, semifinal round.
We have our matchups.
Charlie taking on Ace.
Go.
>> Come on, Charlie.
>> PROBST: The winner moves on
to the final round.
Ace staying alive.
Charlie's got him on the run.
Great match. Ace on the run.
Can he recover?
Charlie's in the water first!
Ace moving on to the final!
Very close.
Now it is Marcus taking on
Randy.
One of you will move on to the
final round.
>> Come on, Randy.
>> PROBST: Randy on the run.
Randy in the water first.
Marcus moving on to the final
round.
All right, next round, Sugar
versus Bob.
We're on.
Winner moves on to the final
round to join Ace and Marcus.
Great match.
Sugar not going anywhere.
Bob slips, trying to hang on.
Bob is back up, a great
recovery.
(Sugar screams)
Bob in the water first.
Sugar moving on.
>> Congratulations!
>> PROBST: The log rolling
champion hits the water first.
You'll be ridiculed back home.
(laughter)
For the final round, all three
of you will be on the log at
the same time.
(groaning)
Take your spots.
For the final round, Ace, we
drew for spots, you got the
middle.
You guys put a foot on the log,
hold it steady.
>> You know, I feel this win is
enormous, so it's important
that I win this challenge.
If I can pull it off, I'll be
proud of myself.
If not, I'll probably shoot
myself in the pinky toe.
>> PROBST: The challenge is on.
Three people on the log at once.
The last person on the log wins
immunity.
Good footwork by all three.
Sugar with a nice save.
Another nice save by Marcus.
Sugar on the run.
Another nice save.
Everybody still alive.
Sugar in the water first!
It's Ace and Marcus fighting
for immunity.
Great battle.
Ace in the water first!
Marcus wins individual immunity.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
(applause)
Marcus, safe at tonight's Tribal
Council.
Now, to the twist, this is yours
to read.
Read it out loud so everybody
can hear it.
>> "You will now assign immunity
to one member of the other
tribe."
I'm going to give this to
Sugar.
>> PROBST: Sugar, come on over.
(applause)
>> My hope is that Sugar is
smart enough to keep the
immunity idol to herself and
that might actually end up
giving us one of our biggest
surprises, which would be
losing a big power player from
the Fang tribe in Ace, Matty,
or Crystal.
>> PROBST: Sugar safe at
tonight's Tribal Council for
Fang.
Marcus is safe for Kota's.
>> When I saw Sugar with the
immunity necklace around her
neck, I'm like, "Damn!
This girl has two idols!"
She is now the most powerful
person in this game.
>> Who would you have picked
from the other tribe to give
immunity to?
>> I don't know.
>> You don't know?
>> Maybe Susie.
>> Susie?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, you think Susie's gonna
be gone tonight?
>> I think that's irritating
people.
>> Oh.
Matty and Ace, they're
thinking to get rid of Crystal
and it all depends on the
pin-up girl, Sugar.
So, yeah, I will lie in this
game.
I will do everything in my
power to get her to vote with
me because my life and Crystal's
life rests upon her.
So, basically, this is honest
to God truth.
This is what's happening around
camp.
I'm not lying to you.
Matty goes, "We're voting out
Sugar next immunity challenge."
And then Crystal's like, "Okay."
So then when Crystal went away,
I looked at Ace, I'm like,
"Are we really voting out
Sugar?"
And Ace is like, "Right now
Sugar is really good for nothing
except for the hidden immunity
idol."
They think you're like
clueless, you're like a dumb
blonde or whatever.
Okay, and Ace thinks he has
you wrapped around his finger.
>> Okay.
I don't trust Kenny, he might
have been lying to me.
But I have been trusting the
biggest snake in the game so
far and I've known that.
So, I really don't know who to
trust at any point in this game.
>> Ace is like, "Well, I
actually got the hidden immunity
idol from her once, I can
probably do that and then we can
blindside her and then I'll have
the hidden immunity idol."
And I was like, "Oh, my freaking
God, this guy is a snake."
>> You and I will say we're
voting on Crystal.
>> We blindside Ace.
>> Blindside Ace today.
>> And we don't have to worry
about the snake ever again.
>> Never again.
>> I trust Sugar and I trust
that she will go along with the
plan to vote out Ace.
She may be the pin-up girl, but
she's very smart.
>> Kenny has reassured me all is
well.
I will truly believe Sugar when
she writes Ace's name down.
Either she's going to write my
name or she's going to write
Ace's name.
>> Why?
Who's going to do that?
They'd only have two votes.
Matty's with you.
>> They'd have three votes.
>> No, it'd be Kenny and
Crystal, wouldn't it?
>> I gave it back to you last
time.
I'll give it back to you this
>> Oh, Ace, I gotta think
about it, okay?
>> That's fine.
>> You make me feel awful.
When Ace asked me for the idol,
it made me think maybe Kenny
was telling me the truth.
>> Don't you think after...
>> Ace definitely knows how to
finagle people much more than
I've ever seen anybody do,
probably in my life.
But he's definitely had my back.
>> I'll bring the last of it,
and then that's it.
>> All right, go for it.
>> Crystal's supposed to go
next, but plans could change.
Ace could be turning on me now.
I have no idea.
Oh, God, what am I gonna do with
this thing?
>> PROBST: Sugar, you've been
out here 21 days.
Tell me about camp life.
What's going on?
>> Um, we are very low on rice.
Crystal accidentally knocked
some over, and she didn't eat
because she knocked it over.
>> PROBST: Kenny, how much rice
did you have before Crystal
knocked it over?
>> We had about seven days
worth.
Crystal ended up scooping some
of the rice that she spilled
outside back into the pot.
So, probably had about five and
a half days worth of rice.
>> PROBST: So, Matty, the rice
is so valuable, that if you
spill even a little in the dirt,
you gotta pick it out grain by
grain.
>> The rice is valuable.
It's the most valuable thing we
have.
We get about six to eight
spoonfuls a day of rice.
>> PROBST: Wow.
>> And she spills the rice, and
nobody goes, "God, Crystal,
what are you doing?!" Nobody...
>> No, but your faces said it
all.
>> Just simmer down.
>> Your face said it all.
>> My face says it all... nobody
says a word to her.
>> Because they knew it was an
accident.
>> Exactly, so just...
>> I didn't purposely go over to
the rice box and just throw the
rice down.
>> Just let me get to my point.
Can I get to my point?
>> Get to your point and then
I'll talk.
>> So, then we looked past it.
We moved past that issue.
>> PROBST: Ace, make sense of
that for me.
>> Crystal made a mistake.
That's common.
The whole part of us feeling
angry at her I thought was a bit
concocted in her own head.
>> Now I'm delusional.
I can see it on your face, Ace.
Okay, don't look at me like
that.
When Matty turned around he was
like, "Oh, whatever."
Then he made some look at you,
Ace.
I didn't say anything to
anybody.
I just sat down there picking up
about 20,000 grains of rice
and then they started to eat.
"Oh, Crystal, come on and eat."
No, I spilled some of the rice
so I will go without and
that's what I did and that's
why I did it.
>> Nobody asked you to, Crystal.
>> It's not like you saved me
any anyways-- you still ate it.
>> I asked you three times...
>> Yeah, I mean, if you cared
enough you would've saved me
some anyways.
>> PROBST: Sugar, you have,
like, the perfect seat in the
midst of this great
Shakespearean drama.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: Your eyes are like
saucers.
>> This sounds like such petty
bull crap to me.
I mean, I think that we can get
past our issues better than
this, and this is why we haven't
been winning, because people are
holding these stupid, petty
things against each other.
>> PROBST: All right, Sugar, you
have individual immunity
tonight.
You can assign that to somebody
else or keep it for yourself.
>> Keeping it.
>> PROBST: Sugar is safe
tonight.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Ace, you're up.
>> You're one of the snakes, and
I got to get rid of you.
Go home.
>> Crystal, I've been waiting
for this day for so long, and I
am so happy it's here.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Ace.
Crystal.
One vote Ace, one vote Crystal.
Ace.
Two votes Ace, one vote Crystal.
We're tied.
Two votes Crystal, two votes
Ace, one vote left.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon...
Ace. That's three.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> PROBST: Ace, the tribe has
spoken.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Well, based on the
reaction from Ace, I'd say that
was a blindside.
21 days in, Fang is finally
starting to play this game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Don't go away.
Coming up next, Kota prepares
for their own Tribal Council.
>> Right now would be an
optimal time to get me out.
>> PROBST: While Dan digs his
own grave...
Susie commits social suicide.
>> I was actually going to vote
you.
>> Really?!
I hate her.
I want her gone, yesterday.
>> Can I ask you a question?
>> What?
>> I'm not going tonight, am I?
>> Not that I know of.
Given the fact that everyone's
voting for Susie.
>> It has to be Susie, 'cause
we have no idea.
We could stay together as a
tribe for another two rounds.
Right now would be an optimal
time to get me out as a strong
player so this is a huge vote
for me, because I'm either going
to come back here and trust
everyone or I'm going to be at
home eating a pizza.
>> Please trust us.
>> Yeah.
>> And, you know...
>> And-and that is incredible
faith on my part, but I know I
got to do it.
>> Randy's replaced Bob in a
final four situation, because I
think Randy's willing to cast
his lot in with a good group of
people, and he's found that.
And he, you know, as long as he
keeps his end of the bargain,
he's got a great run for this
game.
>> She knows she's low man on
the totem pole.
She's bound to.
She may continue to dig her
grave all day long, and-and
y'all's conclusion may shift.
>> Of course.
>> As annoying as Bob is, I see
him as being as loyal and
trustworthy as the day is long.
>> And-and right now, I can't
say the same thing about Dan.
>> I can't, either.
>> But I'm closer being able to
say it about Susie than I am
about Dan.
>> Dan is super vulnerable
tonight.
And the only thing Dan has going
for him right now is that he
should really cross his fingers
that Susie's going to blow up
and do some crazy stuff.
>> I really like you, and I
don't want you to go home.
So I'm not writing your name
down, and I just wanted you to
know that.
You're just not on my list of...
>> Do you know who-who they're
thinking about voting out?
>> Um, I think that it's going
to be Dan.
>> That's what your-- your guess
is it's gonna be Dan?
>> I think so, yeah.
But we felt like we don't want
to take somebody that's gonna
flip.
I feel really good about the
fact that you wouldn't.
>> No, I wouldn't, as long as
you keep me in the loop.
I-I figured people were talking,
and I figured eventually they
would come to me and tell me
where I'm at, you know.
'Cause I-- when I was gonna--
Okay, I'm gonna be honest with
you.
I was actually going to vote
you, because...
>> Why?
>> Because I know that I'm a
hard worker.
I-I know that without having
fire and water and food, how are
you going to perform physically?
You're going to have to take
that time to do that work.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> So I'm just being totally up
front with you, so, and
that's the truth.
>> Okay, so you need me to help
more.
>> Well, yeah, I need help from
everybody, actually.
So that's where I'm at.
But I-I appreciate that, 'cause
now I know which way I can
swing.
>> So this moron has decided
that she'd like me to go.
Really?!
I hate her.
I hate her, hate her, hate her.
Like, I really want to stab her
in the face.
And if you piss me off, you've
pissed off my alliance.
>> Did I not say to you guys
she's nuts?
I mean, certifiable.
>> But she's the worst kind of
nuts, 'cause you don't see it
coming.
>> She goes whichever way the
wind is blowing.
>> Um, I mean, I hate her.
I want her gone, yesterday.
>> Susie's game is no game.
And the problem with no game is
her vote can be bought.
She's gone.
>> Tonight, I don't want any
sort of curveball.
I do not want to go home
tonight.
I don't know what could be
cooking.
I mean, Dan doesn't have the
idol, does he?
>> Not that I know of.
>> What if Susie and Dan get
together, Dan has the idol,
and he's like, "Let's both
vote Corinne"?
>> Then you're gone.
>> Let's just take her out.
Then she has to go.
>> Everybody's ass is on the
line.
Susie needs to go.
She's annoying.
I want her to go home, and soon.
>> So, um, here's the thing.
My entire plan was wedged on the
fact that Susie is easy, she
trusts us, and she's never
gonna win individual immunity.
We can get rid of her when we
want.
I didn't realize she was loco
en la cabeza.
Like, I had no idea that that
was what I was dealing with.
>> I am devastated right now.
>> Well, I'm completely
frustrated, because I feel like
we got some issues that we had
no idea existed.
>> What do you think is the
safer bet?
'Cause I'm really a little
concerned.
>> We're at the point where
I think either decision has
incredible risks associated
with it.
>> Right.
>> Thank God we have a
two-person advantage at this
point.
But Dan could have the
immunity idol.
But I really doubt it, so--
If he actually does have the
immunity idol, we should vote
out Susie.
>> Yeah.
>> Just in case there's an idol.
We're worried that Dan has the
immunity idol, because he spent
a couple days on Exile Island.
But we also think that Dan may
need to go.
So unfortunately, it's not who
is the best asset.
It's who is the least risky.
Which stinks because, you know,
we still don't know who we're
gonna be better off with.
>> PROBST: Marcus, is the game
at a point where you're now
looking out for yourself versus
keeping our tribe strong?
>> I think we're basing our
decision on what we're
expecting to come in the next
few days.
We've got to surround ourselves
with the most powerful crowd of
people, because that's the only
way we're going to survive an
onslaught from the rest of the
Fang tribe.
>> PROBST: Susie, looking at
this tribe, you got to be a
little concerned yourself.
Is it fair to say that you're
the weakest person on this
tribe in challenges?
>> I-I don't think I am.
I think there's certain skills
that I may be a little bit
weaker at, but...
>> PROBST: Who's weaker than
you on this tribe?
>> Um, I think strength-wise,
upper strength, I think I'm
stronger than Corinne.
>> PROBST: Corinne not buying
that at all.
>> I don't want to insult her.
I think that she is very
skilled, and I think that she
does have athletic talent, you
know.
>> PROBST: She just insulted
you.
>> Well, yes, and that's why I'm
telling you that I don't agree.
I think that I have a lot to
offer.
I think I have upper body
strength.
I think I've got a lot of
things, but...
>> And you probably do.
I don't-- I mean, I'm just, I'm
trying to just kind of observe
and just kind of see where this
game's taking me, and...
>> PROBST: Corinne, have you
picked up on Susie's tendencies
to maybe sometimes let loose?
>> Yeah, but I've operated
without a filter for so many
years that, like, I totally
respect when people come out of
their shell and just say
whatever it is that they're
thinking.
I mean, I would encourage more
of that.
Maybe you should blow up once
in a while, and then I'll know
you better.
>> PROBST: Randy, where do you
sit on the "be yourself" versus
"hold it in"?
>> I'm probably about eight on a
scale of ten, and that's good
and bad.
>> PROBST: What's good about it?
>> I don't have to pretend.
And, uh, you know, people pretty
much know where I stand most of
the time.
>> PROBST: What's bad about it?
>> I don't have to pretend, and
people know where I stand most
of the time.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Dan, where do you fit
in on that?
>> Um, I tend to be a
worrywart, and so it has
inhibited me from being
completely comfortable and
completely myself.
But my result in the game will
fare much better if I can shake
it off and just relax.
>> PROBST: Charlie, how big a
factor is trust becoming?
21 days in for this group of
seven.
>> It's huge, because we intend
to go into a merge as a
powerful group together.
And if someone splinters, our
numbers will dwindle before the
Fang numbers dwindle.
So my vote is based on who I can
trust going into a merge most.
>> PROBST: Corinne, is it
possible that tonight's vote
could be a mistake?
>> Damn, yeah.
I don't know if we're making
the right decision or if I
personally am making the right
decision.
I hope that I am.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Marcus, thanks to a nice
performance today, you have
individual immunity.
It is yours unless you choose
to give it to somebody else.
>> We won it for Kota, but I'm
going to hang on to this one.
>> PROBST: All right, you cannot
vote for Marcus.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Bob, you're up.
>> Dan.
Sorry, guy.
>> Susie, you have a, uh, a
great heart, and I'm going to
vote with what I think the rest
of the tribe is voting.
>> This is about Dan, not you.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Susie.
Dan.
Two votes Dan, one vote Susie.
Susie.
We're tied; two votes Susie,
two votes Dan.
Dan.
Three votes Dan, two votes
Susie.
We're tied; three votes Susie,
three votes Dan.
One vote left.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon...
Dan.
Need to bring me your torch.
Dan, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Well, despite being
very successful, this is not
one big, happy family.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
There's a new leader in Africa.
And they call him Randy.
>> I am king of Gabon.
I'm sorry, but I rule.
This ocean, it's mine.
All those Fang and Kota
members, they know the power is
shifting.
I'm king.
Cheers.
>> Whoo!
>> This pretty much blows.
There's a definite level of
disappointment in relation to
Sugar.
Matty, I respect you, you know.
I wish you the best.
C'est la vie.
>> Um, a lot of mixed feelings
right now.
A little bit disappointed that
I didn't make it further in the
game.
On the other hand, it feels
good to be able to be myself.
And I got some great friends and
family to go back to, so that's