>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
With his back against the wall,
Kenny, along with his trusted
ally, Crystal, engineered three
blindsides in a row.
Charlie, the tribe has spoken.
...to create the most powerful
alliance in the game.
>> I'm like a little rat.
I go...
You mess with me, then you're
gone in this game.
>> PROBST: His smartest play was
when he convinced Susie to
switch alliances and join him.
>> It's going down, Kenny.
I knew you were my boy.
>> PROBST: The only potential
roadblocks on his path to the
finals are the two hidden
immunity idols: a real one...
>> Mm. Okay.
>> PROBST: ...owned by Sugar...
>> I found it.
>> PROBST: ...and an
amazing-looking counterfeit
created by Bob.
>> This is my new fake idol.
>> PROBST: If either idol comes
into play, the game changes, and
Kenny's plans could go up in
smoke.
>> It's sort of like when you're
holding up a bank.
You don't necessarily need the
gun.
If they think you got a gun,
they might leave you alone.
>> PROBST: Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Let's get it going, man.
>> That's right.
>> Nobag back in the hizzy.
(laughter)
>> Nobag.
>> Kenny and Crystal know
exactly what's going on in camp.
They know the power is shifting.
>> That was an intense session.
Dude, that was the biggest war
zone yet.
>> Yeah.
(laughter)
>> Everybody better be pretty
happy right here.
>> I thought I was the target
tonight because I was pissing
a whole bunch of people off.
That wasn't the case.
They made more of a smart vote.
Charlie's got a lot of friends.
I don't.
>> 'Cause he's the big threat.
>> He's a good sport.
>> Yes, he is.
>> He's awesome.
He went out with class.
>> And we're in Gabon for
another full moon.
>> I'm gonna do whatever I think
I can do.
When I wake up tomorrow
morning, I'm going to
reevaluate the situation and
hope to come out with something.
I mean, Kenny and Crystal are
taking out my entire alliance.
My chances are very slim.
You know, most likely, me, Bob
and Randy-- we're going to go
home, and we don't know in what
order, but we're going to go
home.
>> It's crazy.
>> Yeah, they just...
>> Like the beginning of the
game again.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Oh, yeah.
(indistinct chatter)
>> I know.
>> But if you have it...
You don't?
>> No.
>> Everybody besides Corinne,
Randy, and Bob know that I have
the idol.
Bob still thinks the idol's out
there.
I kind of feel bad about it,
but it is hilarious.
>> Okay.
>> You did?
>> That does look very good.
You are very creative.
How did you make that, Bob?
>> I stole some of those beads.
I took that resin and put it
down there.
>> Oh, my God, they're awesome.
>> Looks good.
>> That's really good.
>> Fooled you.
>> So...
>> You know, this game is
getting crazy.
Bob has made himself a fake
idol, and he made it out of
resin and beads.
And it's got a little happy face
on it.
I guess Bob might have some kind
of strategy in showing me the
fake immunity idol.
Maybe he's an evil genius.
I don't know.
Just try and... try and relax.
>> You really think it's Susie,
Crystal, and, uh...?
>> Kenny, yes.
>> And-And Kenny in the final
three?
>> Yes, I do.
But I think they've probably
sold that story to Sugar and
Matty, and they're so stupid,
they buy it.
I mean, don't they realize
there's five of them?
They can't all be final three.
>> Yeah.
>> Hello!
>> There's a whole lot of game
left, though, you know?
Corinne is still an ally, but
what can you do with two people?
We've got immunity idols.
We got huge physical threats
like Matty.
Uh, I continue...
I'm planning on just continuing
to be my same charming self.
I don't like any of these
people.
>> I hate them!
>> And I hate them.
And if I pretended to be nice
and like them, like Matty's
doing, I'm not very good at
that.
It would show through, and I
said, the only...
>> You're less damaging to
yourself by just shutting it
down.
>> Yeah. Well-Well, shutting it
down, as well as continue to
being nice.
>> Don't even bother trying to
be nice to Sugar, you know.
Just keep away from them and
work on Matty, and just see if
you can get him to understand
he's going to be on the chopping
block.
>> The hand I have to...
>> Give him the final three with
us.
>> Desperate times call for
desperate measures.
We've got to get somebody to
flip-flop now and come with us,
and that somebody has got to be
Matty because the credibility
of all the others is crap.
>> You guys!
Tree mail has individual
envelopes for everybody!
(gasps and cheers)
>> "Going, going, gone.
He who hesitates is lost.
Nourishment and power.
Everything has its cost."
>> Auction, sounds like.
>> Auction.
>> 500.
>> I'm not going to spend a dime
in the auction unless I get
something that is going to help
me stay in this game.
I mean, that is worth every
penny of $500.
Nothing tastes better than
$500, except a million.
(bird squeaking)
>> PROBST: Welcome to the
Survivor auction.
You each have 500 U.S. dollars.
Bidding will be in increments
of $20.
You cannot pool money.
You cannot share food.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Ready for your first
item?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Beer.
>> Uh-oh!
(laughter)
>> PROBST: And peanuts.
Start the bidding.
>> $20.
>> PROBST: $20 to Randy.
>> $40.
>> PROBST: $40 to Sugar.
>> $60.
>> $80.
>> PROBST: $80 to Sugar.
>> $100.
>> $160.
>> PROBST: Sugar jumps right to
$160.
>> $180.
>> PROBST: Beer looking good?
$180 to Randy.
Going once, going twice.
Sold to Randy.
Three cold bears and peanuts.
>> I don't love beer that much.
I just wanted to up the ante
for him.
>> PROBST: Enjoy.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Next item.
It will remain covered.
>> $100.
>> PROBST: $100 to Kenny.
>> Two even.
>> PROBST: $200 to Randy.
>> $300.
>> PROBST: $300 to Kenny.
>> Ooh!
>> $320.
>> PROBST: $320 to Randy.
>> I think that's all he has.
>> $340.
>> PROBST: $340 to Kenny.
Going once, twice.
Sold to Kenny for $340.
>> Here you go, Jeff.
>> Kenny deserves something
sweet.
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: This is what you just
bought.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Open it up and read
it right here.
Read it out loud.
>> "Send yourself or someone
else to Exile Island.
If you send someone else, you
take all of their money."
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: You have a choice.
You can send yourself...
>> I need a lot of money.
>> PROBST: ...or someone else.
>> Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!
>> I'll take Bob.
>> PROBST: All right, Kenny, go
get Bob's money.
>> I'm sorry, Bob.
When I had the choice to send
anybody to Exile Island, I'm,
like, "Okay, Bob, give me your
money.
I'm sorry, but you can go to
Exile Island."
He doesn't know the idol's not
there 'cause Sugar has it.
And Bob couldn't find it last
time, so he-he wants to give it
another shot to find it.
>> PROBST: Here is a map to
Exile Island.
You will return in time for the
next immunity challenge.
>> Works for me.
>> PROBST: Straight out.
>> All right. Thanks.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Next item up for bid.
>> $100.
>> $120.
>> PROBST: $120 to Matty.
>> $200.
>> PROBST: $200 to Randy.
>> $300.
>> $320.
>> PROBST: $320 to Randy.
>> That's all his money?
>> I think so.
>> He can have it, then.
>> $340.
>> PROBST: $340 to Sugar.
>> Oh, God.
Going once, going twice.
Sold.
Come on up.
>> Hmm.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: $340.
All right, Sugar, this is what
you bought.
>> Yeah!
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God!
>> What is it?
>> Chocolate and peanut butter.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Just what she wanted.
>> Chocolate and peanut butter.
Thank you very much.
>> God.
>> Aah!
>> Chocolate...
>> PROBST: Next item.
A hot bath.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Everything you need
to get clean.
>> Hmm.
>> PROBST: And a clean set of
your clothes.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Kenny.
>> $320.
>> PROBST: Randy doesn't
hesitate.
$320.
>> And get some new clothes.
>> $340.
>> PROBST: $340 to Susie.
>> I bid $100 to bathe her if
she wins.
>> Ew.
>> Yeah, that's not gonna
happen.
>> PROBST: $340 to Susie.
Going once, going twice.
Sold to Susie.
>> You can count it.
>> PROBST: Okay.
>> You should have gone for
that, Kenny.
(laughter)
>> Would you cuddle with a rich
man?
(laughter)
>> Oh!
>> Ooh, yay!
>> Ooh! Yes!
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Ready for your next
item?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: I think everybody
here is going to bid on this
item.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Burger and fries?
>> $100.
>> $120.
>> $140.
>> $320.
>> PROBST: $320 to Randy.
>> $340.
>> PROBST: $340 to Kenny.
>> $400.
>> PROBST: $400 to Matty.
>> You can have it.
>> PROBST: $400.
>> $400 to Matty.
>> PROBST: Once, twice.
Sold to Matty.
Kenny had a lot more money,
passed it up.
$400 for a cheeseburger, fries,
the fixings, and a soda.
>> Oh, and it's on a ciabatta
bun.
>> Oh, man. Nice.
(laughter)
>> I think I'm actually going
to get out, guys.
It's really hot.
>> No, don't get out!
What the hell are you doing,
woman?!
This is the first bath you've
had in 28 days.
>> PROBST: You done in your
bath?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: All right.
>> That's cuckoo.
I would have been there the
whole time.
>> PROBST: Next item will remain
covered.
>> Let's try $100.
>> PROBST: 100 to Kenny.
>> Two even.
>> PROBST: 200 to randy.
>> Keep going.
>> 220.
>> 240.
>> 260.
>> 280.
>> He can have it.
>> PROBST: Kenny, giving it up
again.
>> Yeah, he can have it.
I know it's going to be
something bad.
>> Ooh, Kenny.
PROBST: Sold to Randy, $280.
>> What is that?
>> Ooh, good job, Randy!
>> PROBST: Spaghetti, garlic
bread, and a glass of wine.
>> Sorry, man.
Next item, inside this sealed
bottle is a note.
This note gives you a huge
advantage in the next immunity
challenge.
>> All 500.
>> PROBST: Suddenly, Corinne is
interested.
That makes Kenny the only one
with enough money to outbid her.
>> PROBST: Going once...
Going twice...
>> Yeah?
>> PROBST: Kenny gives it up
again.
Sold to Corinne for $500.
>> I hope it was worth it.
>> PROBST: Here's how this
works.
Take this bottle.
It needs to remain sealed until
I see you at the next immunity
challenge.
>> Okay, thanks.
>> PROBST: Next item: first 20
bucks buys this for the tribe.
>> 20.
>> PROBST: Sold to Randy.
>> He was quick!
>> Thank you, Randy.
>> PROBST: You bought this for
the tribe.
>> How sweet, Randy.
>> PROBST: You just made a lot
of people very happy.
>> Oh, my God!
(cheering)
>> Thank you, Randy!
>> I can have them all to
myself if I want?
>> PROBST: For the tribe, Randy.
>> Okay.
Who wants one?
Would you like one?
>> I don't want one, thank you.
>> Are you sure?
>> I couldn't possibly.
>> Would you like one?
>> Sure.
>> Randy, this is so awesome.
>> Are you sure, Sugar?
>> Matty is getting it.
>> It's not yours to give to
Matty.
I'm the boss.
You can have two, if you'd like.
>> Oh, I'll take one and a half.
Can I do that?
>> Sure.
>> PROBST: So, Randy, you're
giving part of Sugar's to
Corinne?
>> Uh, Sugar doesn't have one.
I offered her one, and she
didn't take one, so, they're
mine.
>> Thank you.
You want half?
>> Yes, please.
>> Go for it.
>> Thank you.
Last chance, you can have a
full one.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Randy offers Sugar
his own cookie.
She takes it and gives it to
Matty.
>> Yeah, would you like to
repeat that?
>> PROBST: Wow.
I think it worked out the way
it worked out.
>> Randy, you at least have to
take this.
>> This is better for me.
>> You sure?
>> PROBST: Well, I'd suggest you
start eating those quickly
'cause the Survivor auction is
over.
>> Sugar-- she can kiss my ass.
If she thinks I was bad before,
I'm just going to turn it up a
notch.
There's a lot of fight left in
this dog.
>> PROBST: Have a good night.
>> Welcome home, Nobag.
(laughter)
>> Check it out.
>> Corinne, I have to say, good
things come to those who wait.
>> That's right.
>> I thought you were blowing
it, but you made the good
decision.
And, Sugar, I have to say, that
was the most righteous gift I've
ever been given.
>> What gift, Matty?
You got to be kidding me.
That wasn't a gift from her,
man.
Weren't you watching?
>> Thought she handed it to me.
>> Yeah, but that was my cookie.
I didn't get one.
>> Oh.
>> You had two, I had none.
>> Sorry.
>> But not your fault.
I left the auction broke, full,
half drunk, and pissed off.
I got a little room left for
one big cookie.
So I'm going to burn this house
down in the next day or so.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Over a cookie.
Over a cookie.
How funny is that?
Oh, my gosh.
Have you ever seen a grown man
get so mad over a chocolate
chip cookie?
And the only reason I took his
damn cookie is because he didn't
want to give me a cookie.
He wanted to give everybody a
cookie but Sugar because
Sugar's evil.
>> How you feeling, big buddy?
Still bitter?
>> Ah, there's no one to talk
to.
Nobody listens to me.
>> What about me?
>> You're busy talking to
everybody else, man.
What we witnessed today at the
auction-- I mean, I was treated
like a dog.
>> You've set yourself up,
Randy.
We've got to drop the attitude
and just be cool.
>> I'm not going to try to talk
to them, any of them.
>> You know, obviously, we're in
a desperate position.
We're three people.
You guys were five.
So, you know that if you, you
know, if you have any kind of
idea, if you'd like to work with
us in any way, we're certainly
open to it.
>> You're on the outs.
The final three in this game is
Kenny, Susie, and Crystal.
Matty's got two ways to play.
He can stay with the original
Fang and go to the finals that
way, or he can come with me and
Corinne and Bob and have a shot
at winning.
>> It's nothing to be ashamed
of.
>> I just arrived at Exile.
I'm going to go for the clue for
the immunity idol, and that's a
real clear choice for me.
The next couple Tribals, there's
a very tight group that are
going to vote Corinne, Randy,
and myself off.
"Across the lake you see so
well, there lies a sandy crater.
The object hidden in its floor
will surely help you later."
Oh, damn.
I realized the extra clue I got
this time was a clue that I'd
already found on my own last
time.
I was a little depressed, but I
got a lot of time here, and what
I'm going to do is, I'm going to
go for my own little safari.
I just think that will be more
rewarding for me than aimlessly
looking around for an idol.
♪ ♪
When I came to Africa, I came
here to experience not only
Survivor, but to sort of learn
about myself, to really think
about how lucky a person I am,
what a wonderful family I have.
It takes your breath away.
And what a beautiful place
Africa is.
I see why they call it the
Garden of Eden.
>> Trying?
Trying?
>> Are you even gonna try?
>> Okay, I'm coming.
I'm going to sit down and
express.
>> Express?
(overlapping chatter)
>> Okay, you guys, we're getting
down to a point where it's
pretty dicey for us.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, so, we-we got to keep
the five of us strong, right?
>> Yes.
>> Randy.
Obviously, it's a no-brainer.
He's set himself up.
He's made his own coffin.
>> Yes...
>> But...
>> But?
>> Bob should go next just to
get him out of the loop, so he
doesn't win immunities and end
our five-some up.
Randy's not going to win any
challenges.
Corinne's not going to win any
Bringing them in to the final
final six, final seven is way
safer for us.
I think Bob should go next.
>> I'm noticing now that Matty
is really playing the game and
that he is trying to take
control, and that he is a
physical threat, and he's trying
to get rid of Bob, who is the
other physical threat, and hang
on to Randy for some reason.
Is he going to join up with
Randy 'cause he's wizening up
and know that it's smart to have
a jerk at the end?
>> We got to have a plan, so it
it has to be Bob.
>> Okay.
>> It has to be Randy, then
Corinne.
Bob, Randy, Corinne.
>> Okay.
>> That's the order.
>> Then we're down to the four.
>> It sucks.
>> I know it sucks, but stop...
>> Hello!
>> Okay, fine.
>> Here he is.
Here-Here he comes.
Here he comes.
Bob, Randy, Corinne.
>> I know.
>> Good morning, sunshine.
>> What you got for me?
>> FYI, I'm crashing and burning
today.
>> I love this.
>> I stayed up all night just
thinking of the most diabolical
thing that we could do to keep
us in the game and get the worst
person in this game out.
Corinne, myself, and Bob are on
the outside.
Our only chance is to shake
things up.
I'm going to be crashing and
burning all day, make everybody
miserable, showing these
morons...
Just putting them in their
place.
The plan is for me to act really
nasty, continue to mix it up
with everybody, and the old Fang
people are going to vote for me.
Our only prayer is if Bob would
give me the idol.
>> This is a good idea.
>> Everyone vote me out.
I spring the idol out at Tribal.
Susie is three votes, and goes
home.
>> I love it.
>> It's our only prayer.
>> That's a great plan.
>> We get the feeling that Bob
probably found the immunity
idol, and the plan is to
convince Bob to give me the
hidden immunity idol.
I play the idol.
Voilà-- Susie, joke's on you.
You're going home.
>> So, think about it, enjoy the
thought. Yeah.
>> I don't need to think about
it.
I'm-I'm totally on board.
I'm going to talk to Bob...
>> I mean, it buys us three more
days, and something new could
happen.
>> I will talk to Bob.
Let me see if I can get Bob on
board.
>> You like it?
>> I love it.
>> I not only want Susie to go
home, but I want to blindside
her.
The reason that myself and
Corinne and Bob are in the
predicament we are in is because
Susie flipped.
She went with Crystal and Kenny,
and they voted Marcus out.
That's part of the game, but the
hell with her.
Uh, this would be sweet, sweet
revenge.
(Randy imitates yawning)
>> Why do you have to tell the
world?
>> There's not a...
There's not a normal person
among them, except you, and you
even... even whored yourself
out.
>> Oh, my God.
Don't do this, dude.
Don't.
>> You know you have.
You know, I don't blame you.
It's worth a million dollars to
you.
It's not to me.
>> Oh, my God.
Randy just sealed his fate, you
know.
I've done what I can.
And if you're not going to
listen to what I have to say or
take my advice, then, I mean,
there's nothing I can do.
It's a no-brainer that Randy
has to go home now, and he's
going out with a bang.
>> Guess how many of those
cookies I ate?
>> Those freaking cookies.
>> I was in charge of every
single one of them, but I didn't
get any.
It-it was for the tribe, and I
could do anything-- I could put
it in the dirt and stomp on it,
if I wanted to.
>> I got the impression that you
really didn't want to give it...
>> To anybody.
>> I'm tired of this story.
>> Thank you.
>> You're right.
I'm done.
>> Then shut the (bleep) up.
>> I can talk when I want.
>> Randy got to go.
Randy needs to go.
He is a troll.
He is wreaking havoc in the
Nobag tribe.
>> That man.
>> He's going home.
>> Oh, yeah, doesn't matter.
>> I like where I'm sitting
right now.
They're all freaking out.
And that's a real good thing.
The more they freak out, the
more paranoia sets, the more
Operation Strong-arm can be
effective.
Man, we've still got an immunity
challenge to play.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Bob returning
from Exile Island.
>> How's it going, Bob?
>> Good morning, gang.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first--
take back the necklace, Susie.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
race across a series of balance
beams carrying a bag of puzzle
blocks.
When you reach the finish,
you'll head back to the start,
do it again.
The first two people to get
their three bags across the
line move on to the final round.
In the final round, you will
empty your bags filled with
puzzle blocks.
You must arrange those puzzle
blocks along a multi-angled
platform while avoiding trip
wires which could tip your
blocks, forcing you to start
over.
>> Mmm.
>> PROBST: Your goal is to
arrange your blocks so they will
fall one into another like
dominoes, raising a flag.
First person to raise their flag
wins immunity, is guaranteed a
one-in-seven shot at winning
this game and a million dollars.
Losers, Tribal Council.
Somebody will be voted out.
Corinne, at the auction, you
bought an advantage in today's
immunity challenge.
You have the bottle?
>> Please be something magical.
This is good.
"You will sit out for the first
stage of this challenge and
move directly into the final
round."
>> PROBST: Huge advantage in
this challenge.
>> Thank you!
>> PROBST: Corinne is now
guaranteed a one-in-three shot
at winning this challenge and
staying alive in this game.
Corinne gets to sit out the
first round.
Everybody else, we'll get
started.
Here we go.
For immunity, first two people
to finish move on to the final
round.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Matty off to a quick start.
Matty doesn't hesitate, has his
first bag across.
Kenny has his first bag across.
It is Matty and Kenny.
Bob is across.
Susie's across.
Matty across with his second
bag.
Sugar, no good, gotta go back.
Here comes Kenny with his second
bag.
Matty's got his final bag.
Susie with her second bag.
Kenny makes it with his second
bag.
Bob falls off, no good.
Gotta go back.
Matty's across with three bags.
Matty's moving on.
Susie has her second bag.
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Sugar and Crystal
fall.
One spot left to get to the
final round.
Who's going to get it?
Kenny with a big leap.
Kenny moves on to the final.
It is Kenny, Matty, and Corinne
in the final round.
All right, in the final round,
Kenny, Matty, Corinne.
For immunity, survivors, ready?
Go!
Your job is to arrange those
puzzle blocks like a nice line
of dominoes.
Matty, Corinne, starting at the
front.
Kenny moving to the end, working
his way backwards, three
different strategies.
Where this challenge gets tricky
is when you have to start
maneuvering with those trip
ropes.
One wrong move on those trip
ropes could knock over
everything you've built so far.
Corinne making a lot of
progress.
Matty seems to have the early
lead.
Corinne taking her time.
Kenny's pieces go down.
Kenny may have made it more
difficult, starting at the end.
Matty very close to knocking
everything over.
Kenny picking up his fallen
pieces.
Corinne making a lot of
progress.
Question is: have you spaced
them properly?
Matty has a bit of a lead if
he's right.
Corinne still in it.
Kenny and Matty arranging their
last pieces.
Matty has two blocks left.
If he's wrong, it's a lot of
work for nothing.
Kenny gathering his last blocks.
Kenny coming on strong now.
Suddenly, Kenny's nearly
complete.
Everybody's still in this
challenge.
>> Jeff, I got it.
>> PROBST: Kenny's going to give
it a shot.
>> Push it?
>> PROBST: Push it.
>> Come on!
Go! Go!
>> PROBST: Kenny's doesn't work.
He's got to rearrange it.
Matty now heading back.
Do not panic!
Take your time!
Corinne now looking good.
Corinne, by being calm, has kept
herself in this challenge.
Matty has placed all his blocks.
Is he ready to give it a try?
>> Ready to give it a try, Jeff!
>> All right, I'm going to try
it again, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Kenny's ready to give
another shot.
>> I'm trying it, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Corinne is now going.
Matty's in on it.
This is it right here.
Everybody has their blocks
moving.
Who is going to finish first?
Matty's halfway through.
Kenny's looking good.
Million dollars on the line.
Does it go, Corinne?
>> Almost.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
>> PROBST: No, Corinne's stopped
short.
Matty's doesn't go.
>> Go! Go! Go!
>> PROBST: Kenny wins immunity!
Kenny, come on over.
Congratulations.
With this around your neck, you
are safe at tonight's Tribal
Council.
As for the rest of you, after 30
days, this game will come to an
end for one of you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Congratulations.
>> Randy and I needed to win.
Now, I'm going on a wing and a
prayer that Bob has the idol.
I just need to figure out if he
has it or not.
I was so close.
♪ ♪
>> I can't believe it.
>> I can.
It's awesome!
>> Hey, Kenny, good job.
Very good job.
>> Yeah, thanks, guys.
>> Good job, bro.
>> Matty was like so close, too.
That was insane.
>> I am 75% sure that I need the
idol tonight because they're
going to vote for me.
Ideally, tonight, Bob gives me
the idol, and whoever Corinne,
Bob, and I decide to send home
will be going home.
Right now, it looks like Susie.
>> Okay.
Well, I... that's what I kind of
feel like now, too.
>> I really would feel guilty if
Bob went home and I stayed.
But if he even semi-offers it,
I'm going to take it.
>> I know you guys aren't going
to believe me if I tell you I
don't have the idol.
And you-you have to...
>> It wouldn't matter.
I do believe you.
I have your best interests in
mind.
Um, you can vote for whoever you
want, but it might behoove you
to vote against Randy.
>> We don't need him here.
>> Yeah, I know.
And it might buy you some time,
and if it doesn't buy you some
time, I got another plan.
Randy is an ass, and I loathe
him with every inch of my being.
>> Thanks, sweetie. Bye.
>> Bye.
The guy is a bigot.
He offends everyone.
And maybe that's his game, but
I'm not even worried about that
because Randy's gone.
You didn't tell anybody that
you didn't find it, right?
I think that Randy would fall
for it.
Your idol.
>> If I give him the fake one?
>> And it... it would be
hilarious.
>> If you think he'd fall for
it, but I just, you know...
>> Yeah, don't worry.
>> If we figure out a way for me
to give it to Randy, I will do
that.
Sugar wants to play the joke on
Randy.
My life expectancy is a little
bit better off allowing her to
have the satisfaction of me
giving Randy the-the idol.
I've got nothing to lose.
It's not a real idol.
I can't save myself with it.
The only way I can save myself
for another Tribal Council is by
convincing somebody else to use
it, and I think it should do the
trick.
>> I want to run through the
options with you.
Okay, obviously, the only Hail
Mary we've got is the idol,
which I assume you found.
Okay.
And you know you cannot tell
anybody you found the idol, at
all.
Other than me or Randy, you
cannot trust anybody, especially
not Sugar.
Obviously, if you found the
idol, the smartest strategy
would be to give it to Randy
if you thought that Randy was
getting voted out 'cause it
would save us.
>> If at the end of the day, I
think they're going to go for
Randy...
>> You're going to give it for
Randy.
>> I'm going to give it to Randy
and the three of us vote for
Susie.
>> Yeah, no matter what, the
three of us vote for Susie.
I love you.
Thank you for coming back.
And thank you for finding the
idol.
>> That was...
>> I'm trying to figure out
what to do.
What I'm thinking is you've
pissed everybody off so much...
>> I'm going tonight.
>> If I gave you that idol...
>> Bob has not only told me that
he has the idol, but he showed
it to me.
I saw it.
It was two feet away from me.
I am thrilled that Bob found
the idol.
I'm especially thrilled that
he's willing to give it over to
me.
>> The hit is on Susie.
>> Susie, yeah.
>> Make sure Corinne and-and...
all I can offer you now is, if
you're in the finals and I'm
not, you got my vote for a
million.
>> Save some starch for me when
we...
>> It's a deal.
We got word that the hit is on,
on me tonight, so Bob did one of
the most, uh, selfless acts I've
ever seen, which was, uh, to
give me his hidden immunity
idol.
There is going to be some
surprised people tonight, I
think, and I'm here for three
more days.
Looks like an idol to me.
>> You're a genius.
I cannot believe you did that.
I cannot wait to see this.
You are awesome.
Thank you.
>> Make it worth my while.
>> Oh, I will.
Don't worry.
I'm making it worth your while.
You kick butt, dude.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: I'll now bring in the
members of our jury.
Marcus and Charlie, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Let's start with the auction.
It ended with what should have
been a happy note.
Randy buys a plate of chocolate
chip cookies for the tribe, but
it didn't go down so smoothly.
Sugar, what was your take on
how it all played out?
>> Well, Randy offered me his
last cookie, which I wasn't
really thinking about it being
his last cookie.
I just thought that they were
for the tribe, and so I took it,
and I gave it to Matty, and
we've heard about it for three
days.
>> PROBST: Randy, looking back
on your actions, did you play it
the right way?
Was that appropriate?
>> It wasn't the last cookie.
It was my cookie.
And honestly, I was testing her.
I could have thrown them on the
ground and stomped on them if I
wanted to, or I could have been
generous like I was.
>> PROBST: So you think their
reaction was maybe a little
harsh because you did offer
everybody a cookie?
>> Yes, and I even offered Sugar
one twice.
>> It's freaking cookies.
My God, we're grown-ups.
It's stupid.
>> PROBST: Susie, why is this
seemingly funny story about a
cookie so representative of this
game?
>> You're really getting to know
people's true colors and what
they're really like 'cause I
have actually questioned,
thinking, "God, you know, is
Randy really like this?"
He's actually probably a person
that's really hurting.
I feel kind of sorry for him
because he probably is very sad.
>> You know, actually, saying "I
feel sorry" for somebody is
another way of saying, "How
pathetic."
>> Oh, my apologies.
I don't mean it that way.
>> And I was totally sincere
with the cookie, too.
I swear I was.
That's why I went off today.
So...
>> PROBST: Corinne, it sounds
like something happened at camp
today.
Randy says he went off.
What happened?
>> I don't even know what
started it, but all of a sudden,
I hear something to the effect
of, "Shut up," directed from
Randy at Susie.
And it's a very awkward thing
to be sitting through.
>> PROBST: Crystal, can you feel
the tension ramping up as we get
into the very tail end of this
game?
>> I sure can feel the tension
ramping up.
Like, for instance, the cookie
conversation that exploded into
a blatant disrespect to a grown
woman... to me, under any other
circumstances, that's hands down
for a slap.
>> PROBST: Is there any chance
that Randy's playing some sort
of game?
>> If-if... if this is him, then
he's giving it to me raw.
And I will never talk to him
outside of this situation.
But if this is his game and no
one's going to possibly reject
me and I'm going to get to the
end, then that's his game.
>> PROBST: Bob, let's talk about
your second trip to Exile
Island.
Is anybody brave enough to bring
up the notion of the hidden
immunity idol?
>> Oh, oh, yeah, yeah.
I made a point of not letting
people know for sure whether I
had it or I didn't have it
because it's part of the game.
And I'm here to play.
>> PROBST: Randy, I know you're
worried every time you come to
Tribal, but with so much
animosity directed toward you,
how worried are you tonight?
>> You're wrong about one thing.
I haven't been worried every
time I come to Tribal.
And I am a bit worried tonight,
though.
You're right about that.
But 30 days is a pretty good
run.
>> PROBST: So, if it's you
tonight, you're okay with that?
>> No, I would not be okay with
leaving.
I want to stay.
>> PROBST: With that, it is time
to get to the vote.
Kenny, you have the individual
immunity necklace.
You can keep it for yourself or
give it to somebody else.
>> I will keep it tonight, Jeff.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Kenny.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Matty, you're up.
>> I'm voting you, Susie,
'cause payback's a bitch.
>> You are a disgusting, old,
hotheaded, chauvinistic,
alcoholic bigot, and you need to
grow up before you die alone.
And a loser.
>> This vote is not strategic.
It's strictly personal.
>> (loudly): You have made my
life hell from day one!
Forget you!
Go home!
Good-bye.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
>> PROBST: Thank you.
The rules of Survivor state that
if a hidden immunity idol is
played, then the votes cast
against that person will not
count, and the person with the
next highest number of votes
will be voted out.
This is not a hidden immunity
idol.
(laughing)
All votes cast against Randy
will count.
I'll now read the votes.
First vote... Randy.
Randy-- two votes Randy.
Susie.
Two votes Randy;
two votes Susie.
That's three votes Susie;
two votes Randy.
Randy.
That's three votes Randy;
three votes Susie.
Randy.
That's four votes Randy;
three votes Susie.
One vote left.
11th person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon, and the third
member of our jury: Randy.
Need to bring me your torch.
Randy, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, after tonight's Tribal
Council, it's very clear this
game is coming down to one
thing: trust.
Can't wait to see how it plays
out.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Being voted out by these
bozos is probably one of the
best accolades anyone could get.
The hell with these freaking
people.
I hope Corinne does well if she
was not in on today's plot, and
I don't think she was.
You know, most of the others,
with the exception of Matty, I
hope they get bit by a green