>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Deep in the heart of Africa, two
tribes have been battling.
Nobody on the Fang goal!
How does that happen?
Kota, the yellow tribe, has won
six out of eight challenges and
lives very well.
>> Life is good.
>> The rich are definitely
getting richer here at Kota.
>> PROBST: Fang, the red tribe,
has struggled with everything,
and squandered most of their
food.
>> It's the Goof Troop.
It's ridiculous.
>> PROBST: At Fang, Ace and
Sugar were tight with each other
and no one else.
And Sugar had the hidden
immunity idol.
>> I trust you.
>> PROBST: So when the rest of
Fang discovered the idol, they
agreed that Sugar and Ace were
the next to go.
>> See ya, beeyotch.
>> PROBST: The two outsiders got
a temporary reprieve when GC
got tired of the game and said
he couldn't go on.
>> He came up to me and said
that he's just done with this.
He's had enough.
>> PROBST: The tribe saw his
weakness and voted him out.
GC, the tribe has spoken.
Can Fang turn it around?
And can Ace and Sugar survive
another Tribal Council?
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(metal striking repeatedly)
>> Nice!
>> Yay, Matty!
>> Ah, I'm so happy.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> It's just, like, positive
energy now; we're all positive.
Nobody is dragging.
>> You know, tonight was
particularly hard.
>> Yeah, tonight was hard.
>> Tribal Council is sad.
You know, not unexpected.
Um... GC had to go.
I've got Sugar in my pocket, and
I need to try and arrange
something that I can save myself
until merge.
I just don't know who would be
my potential Benedict Arnold.
>> (sings indistinctly)
>> Good morning.
>> How'd you sleep?
>> Not very good.
I was, like, up all night.
>> That's crazy, dude.
>> I know what means the most to
me in my life.
Every night I dream about food,
my dog, and my girlfriend.
Every night.
This is by far the hardest thing
I've ever done.
But... my whole driving force
out here is Jamie-- she's my
girlfriend-- so I'm trying to
make some sort of ring-type
thing.
It's just something to keep
myself reminded of her.
Because of her, I want to finish
this out to the end.
I'm in a terrible position, and
I feel like I've been in a bad
position the moment this game
started with Fang.
If somebody approached me with
a legitimate, logical,
reasonable plan that might
work, for sure I'm on board,
man.
I am jumping on board and I'm
flying with it.
♪ ♪
Come over here.
What do you think?
>> I'm just stressed, man.
>> Why?
>> Man, I just want to make it
as far as possible, you know?
>> You know, I just... I prefer
not to be blindsided.
>> It all just depends on how
close everyone is, you know?
I mean, you want to keep Kenny
around?
Or Crystal, and all them?
>> Kenny.
>> I mean, I-I don't really want
Sugar to go.
You've got your Kenny, I've...
>> That's fine.
Okay, that's cool.
That's the deal.
>> Deal?
>> Deal. I got my Kenny, and you
got your Sugar.
>> Until merge, you're...
on your girl, you're not
gonna stab me in the back.
>> Okay.
>> I'll... I can guarantee I'm
with you.
>> Okay, what do you have to put
it on, then?
>> My mother's life.
>> Your mother's life that
you're gonna get me to...
>> Yeah, same as your girl's.
>> Okay, I'll put it on my girl,
then.
>> Okay?
>> All right.
>> I mean, that's huge.
My mother's my best friend.
>> My girl's my everything.
I think Ace and I are probably
some of the top competitors out
here physically, and I do like
him on my side, and... I made a
pact with Ace that I can't
break, and I promised on my
girlfriend, which is the love of
my life.
She's my driving force out here,
and I'm not gonna break that
promise for a million dollars.
Not for $5 million.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
(elephant trumpeting)
>> I know I look like Oliver,
but... sorry.
>> What's on that menu?
>> Don't drink, or drink at your
own risk.
>> That's the sushi plate?
>> Randy.
Are you gonna eat off this one?
>> Yeah.
>> We might have to share
together, Bob.
>> Yep. It works.
We've been eating very well, and
when we got spices and salt, we
started eating quite a bit.
But Dan was shoveling it on with
a spoon, and I realized when I
served Susie and I, I put the
same number of scoops on my
plate for Susie and I to share
as Dan put on for himself.
>> It doesn't matter if you
weigh a hundred pounds more than
me, you've still got the same,
like, proportion of food.
But Dan's decided that he
deserves fourth and fifth
servings of food.
(indistinct chatter)
So now we are going through food
at an alarming rate, and he
takes... multiple servings.
I'm sick about how much food is
being wasted on him.
(frustrated grunt)
♪ ♪
>> Well, what do you guys think?
You think there's enough rice to
get through nine days?
>> Here's the thing.
We could do two small.
Say you want... or one big one
later?
>> So whatever you guys think,
man.
That's better for digestion:
we get two small meals.
>> Cooking small, it's not that
good 'cause a lot of it sticks
to the side.
>> I agree.
>> Starting on day one, I was
talking about how everybody does
not reserve the right to just
eating it raw and... and just
spilling it all over the place,
and now, of course, we have a
shortage of rice.
We have about six days' worth.
If we don't have rice, we're
dead.
Basically, we're gone.
It's hard for our tribe right
now.
It's, like, we're at rock
bottom.
>> Hello there.
>> Hello.
>> Why?
>> Yeah. Um...
Right?
I was trying to hang on to my
idol as long as possible, but
Ace came and told me that he
thinks they've gone through my
bag and found it.
So I gave it to Ace for
safekeeping.
Ace is now in possession of the
idol.
He's got it in his pocket.
I'm really putting a lot of
faith in Ace right now.
Ace is kind of a snake, but he's
my snake, and I'm glad to have
him.
>> It's been a crazy couple of
days.
It went from me being in a
position of no power to a
position of supremacy, having
the immunity idol in my pocket.
I have Matty's word.
I have Sugar.
I feel like I've put myself in a
very good position, coming from
a tribe that I didn't have any
alliance with.
And now suddenly, you know,
I've got people there.
(elephant trumpets)
Oh, my God, this is amazing.
I just turned around and
there's an elephant swimming
through the water.
Oh, how beautiful.
I guess that's one way to get
from one side to the other.
(trumpeting)
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Kota getting your first look at
the new Fang tribe.
>> (whispers): Jeez... God.
>> PROBST: GC voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, each tribe will be
tethered to a 20-foot-long,
200-pound snake.
You will start on opposite sides
of the course.
On my "go," you will race around
the course attempting to catch
the other tribe.
If along the way you get tired
and become a liability, you can
opt out of the challenge by
simply disconnecting from the
snake.
That will force the rest of your
tribe to pick up that extra
weight.
First tribe to catch the other
tribe and touch one tribe
member wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes. Absolutely.
>> PROBST: I think you're gonna
like it.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Croissants, fruit
tarts, chocolate éclairs, plus
everything you need to make a
nice cup of coffee... or a hot
pot of tea.
In addition, the winning
tribe'll send one member of the
losing tribe to Exile Island.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah. Yes.
>> PROBST: Kota, you have one
extra member, sitting somebody
out, keeping in mind you cannot
sit out the same person in
back-to-back challenges.
>> I'll sit out.
>> PROBST: Corinne's gonna sit
this one out.
Corinne, take a spot on the
bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Kota.
>> PROBST: Huge reward on the
line.
This challenge is going to be
won by the tribe that wants it
the most.
>> They're turning the corner.
They've got a few steps on us.
>> We're gaining on them, guys.
Come on.
>> Keep this pace.
Keep this pace.
>> Take it easy.
>> Come on, Kota!
You guys got this.
>> PROBST: Fang gets an early
lead off the start.
>> We're all right.
>> All right, downhill here.
Go.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: Think about those
pastries, that hot cup of
coffee.
It would be nice to wake up to
some of that.
>> Keep it up, Kelly.
>> PROBST: Kelly barely moving.
>> Kelly, they're catching up.
>> I'm coming.
>> PROBST: Kota now gaining on
Fang after one lap of this
course.
You're going to get tired.
You're going to want to quit.
Every time somebody drops out,
you put a bigger burden on the
rest of your tribe.
>> If you got to drop, drop.
Then we'll move.
>> Kota gaining more ground on
Fang.
>> All right, guys.
Here we go.
>> Come on!
>> We've got to speed up.
>> We got to move!
>> PROBST: Kota continues to
make up ground.
>> We're gaining on them.
>> PROBST: Fang is fading very
quickly.
>> Drop half the people and we
sprint.
Go. Just get off.
>> Okay.
>> Sugar, go. Kenny, go.
>> Run!
>> PROBST: Sugar and Kenny both
drop out, and that seems to
help Fang.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: They're now moving
much more quickly.
>> Put 'em down right now.
>> Go, Kelly. Get out of here.
Just unhook.
>> PROBST: Kelly has now dropped
out.
>> Let's do this!
>> PROBST: Fang is down to
three members.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Susie drops out for
Kota.
Fang now getting some distance
on Kota now that they've lost
Kenny and Sugar and Kelly.
>> I'm getting tired.
>> PROBST: Crystal is starting
to drag now.
>> They're dragging.
Come on!
>> PROBST: Matty pushing her.
Frustrated.
>> Crystal, just drop out if you
can't do it!
>> PROBST: Crystal now drops
out.
>> I can't take all that
weight, Matty.
>> Come on. Let's go!
>> PROBST: It's all on Matty
and Ace.
Big opening for Kota now.
>> Yeah, you've got this!
>> PROBST: Kota with five
strong guys going up against
Matty and Ace, who are
struggling.
>> Come on the side of me!
Come on the side of me, man!
(grunting)
Come on, grab it!
>> PROBST: Matty carrying half
that snake himself.
Ace dragging the other half.
Ace trying to keep his pants up!
Kota closing in on a big win
and a huge reward.
>> Yeah!
Yeah!
>> PROBST: Kota wins reward.
>> Yeah!
>> Not even close.
Not even close.
Nice.
>> You all right, Bob?
>> Oh, God.
>> If I can do it at your age...
>> PROBST: Kota,
congratulations.
This reward has enough for you
to sample a little now and
still have plenty to take back
to camp.
>> Can you share?
>> Can we have one?
>> Uh, no.
>> Everyone grab one of these.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
>> Ooh, I want some
strawberries.
>> Mmm!
>> Crystal, what hurts more,
losing or seeing this tempting
array of food in front of you
and knowing you can't have it?
>> Losing over and over.
(sniffles)
It's starting to hurt.
>> PROBST: Something you're not
used to.
>> No.
>> Waah, waah, waah!
>> PROBST: All right, Kota, who
are you going to send from Fang
to Exile Island?
>> Sugar.
>> PROBST: Sugar, for the
fourth time, you'll be sent to
Exile Island.
Sugar, you will return in time
for the next immunity challenge.
Fang, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> I love winning challenges.
More importantly than winning
challenges, I absolutely love
watching them lose.
>> PROBST: Kota,
congratulations.
Come get your reward.
>> Randy? To me, he's just...
He's a troll.
He's a troll under the bridge
that's just mean and angry with
the world.
I don't play like that.
Do not disrespect me like that.
I have a feeling that in the
event there's a merge, that
old Fang and new Fang won't
get along.
>> No pun intended, but sweet.
>> Today's challenge just showed
that Kota is a strong, unified
team.
And I'm so excited to see that.
I mean, when it works like a
charm in the challenges, there's
just no better feeling.
>> I think we need a table to
sit down and have breakfast at.
>> Has anyone thought about how
we want to split this up?
>> Charlie had a great idea.
Split it up, and each
individual person can just eat
their share as they want.
>> Well, I know that, um, there
are definitely seven
croissants and there's seven
of these jelly things.
>> Okay.
>> And then we could figure out
how many's in the middle.
>> So, if someone doesn't want
an eclair, they can get an
extra one of these.
If someone doesn't want
a Cinnabon, they can get one
of those.
>> If it wasn't for Dan, we
wouldn't have rationing laws,
so when the pastries came
back, like, the old Kota
members like me, Marcus, and
Charlie are already like, "How
are we going to divide this?"
So we tried to make it as fair
as possible.
>> This will be...
>> This should just be gravy.
>> What do you mean gravy?
>> Extra.
Go with the original plan, which
was cook dinner and, um, you
know, this is just...
>> Yeah, 'cause that will give
us one more meal on the back
end.
>> Exactly.
>> That's why it's a good idea.
>> I don't want to be hungry
come midnight.
>> Dan, he has annoyed
everybody.
He's even annoyed me a little
bit.
>> This is so good.
I can't stop.
>> Yeah, it does.
It feels so good when it hits
my lips.
>> My best move might be to
just kind of slowly distance
myself from Dan as I bring
myself closer to the original
Kota.
>> God, those pastries are good.
>> Go for it.
>> If I take one bite, I only
have one and a half left.
>> It's a reward.
There's no rationing.
>> Don't do that.
>> I knew that they were
probably going to send me back
to Exile.
This is lame.
Why-why...
Why do I get to come back here
and...
Eat fruit when everybody is
starving at my tribe, and
they're running out of food,
and they don't have anything
but rice.
And I'm feeling really guilty.
I just feel bad knowing that I
already have the idol.
Actually, I gave Ace the idol in
case he needs it before Tribal,
but...
Well, we'll see if that happens.
>> I wouldn't mind getting some
more of the fruit.
>> Hey, this is my opinion.
Today it's super mellow out.
>> Re-hydrate.
>> Tomorrow we're going to have
a big day, and it's probably
going to be super hot.
So we might as well get
everything done today, get all
the canteens filled.
>> I don't know why you're
stressing over it.
>> I'm not stressing.
>> Yes, you are.
>> Fang lost another challenge.
We needed that food because
I'm, like, withering away, and
we have, like, three scoops
of rice.
And then, Crystal's reaction
of our loss was huge.
She just, like, broke down in
tears.
Personally, I just think her
personality sucks.
>> I know.
Like, seriously, that all just,
like, sucks.
It's like a damper on the team.
Like, you don't need to cry,
right?
>> Well, it's just a different
sort of cry than uh...
Sugar's cry is more a...
>> Emotional.
>> Emotional, I'm happy to be
here.
>> Right.
>> Don't view my tears at
today's challenge as a sign of
weakness.
Because it's far from that.
You and Kelly view me as weak
now because I was crying?
>> Not weak.
>> Where did they go, up by the
hill or they went by tree mail?
>> By tree mail and by the hill.
>> I hope that they don't put
me in the same category as GC,
someone that wants to give up.
Because shortly after I got
back to camp, I snapped out of
my funk.
But Kelly hasn't had two words
to say to me, and so now she's
going to feel the wrath of
Crystal.
>> Hey, how did you get here?
>> Same way you got here.
>> Really?
>> She walked.
>> Are you feeling better?
>> Yeah, I mean, y'all have
already had the comforts of
food.
I mean, you guys have had fish.
I've had a pinch of a freaking
sardine.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> But, like I tell you and like
I tell everybody else in my
tribe: don't mistake my tears
as a sign of weakness because
at some point, we all get
depressed.
It's just that mine come out
through my eyes, you know.
I mean, I think I can still
battle with the best of them
and just don't mistake it as a
sign of weakness because it's
not.
But I'm fine now.
>> I definitely think that
Crystal crying in front of
the Kota tribe and our tribe, it
shows a sign of weakness.
Like, you could take it
either which way, you know.
Like, she can explain it to us,
but she can't explain it to the
Kota tribe.
>> I think more so with me, it
wasn't the danish, it was the
pride.
>> It just sucks,
especially when you lose,
and we lose every time.
>> Marcus.
A giant turtle.
>> A giant turtle?
>> Not giant, but big enough.
>> Okay, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
Let me give you my shirt or
something.
Untie me.
I'll bring the boat around.
>> Your hands are too important.
Hold on.
>> Listen to me.
I don't want you to lose your
hand.
>> It doesn't matter.
It's food.
>> Whoo!
>> All right, we've got a
turtle!
I was really excited because it
was like winning a reward
challenge, except we did it
ourselves, so it had that extra
bit of joy to it.
>> That is neat.
>> You know...
You know how to cook that,
right?
>> That's good size.
>> Kill it and then crack the
shell, break it out, and cut it
in cubes and boil it.
>> Wow.
>> Go for it.
I'm excited about it.
I think it's going to taste
good.
Have you ever had gumbo turtle
soup here in the jungles of
Africa?
How cool is that?
>> It's going to be delish.
I know it.
>> That's delicious.
>> That is so good.
Mmm.
>> I can't complain.
>> Right now, the Kota tribe is
probably at our highest high.
The fact that we caught a
turtle has just knocked us up
ten notches.
Fang better watch out.
>> (muffled): I love it.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Sugar,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Howdy.
>> Hi.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first.
You're hiding it back there,
Charlie.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, each
tribe will divide into three
pairs.
Each pair will be tethered
together by rope.
On my go, the first pair will
crawl under a cargo net, race
into the jungle, navigate an
obstacle and retrieve two
sections of a flagpole, then
race back.
Then the next pair goes.
Each leg of the challenge adds
another obstacle, making it
more difficult.
First tribe to collect all
three pairs of flagpole pieces
and assemble it correctly wins
immunity.
Safe at least one more day in
this game.
Losers, Tribal Council,
somebody going home.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Kota, you have one
extra member.
You're going to have to sit
somebody out.
Who's it going to be?
Susie, you're going to sit this
one out?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Take a spot on the
bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you
a minute to pair up, and we'll
get started.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Bob and Randy for Kota
and Kelly and Sugar for Fang.
>> Nice, Sugar, nice, Kelly!
>> PROBST: Kelly and Sugar
getting through the course
quickly.
Randy dragging it for Kota.
Fang looking strong.
Sugar against Bob on the ropes.
Who's going to have the most
nimble fingers, get that first
flag sections?
Bob has their flagpole
sections down.
Sugar has hers down!
Got to unclip and get back.
Randy and Bob heading out.
Kelly and Sugar right behind.
>> Let's go, guys.
>> Come on. Hustle it out!
>> Halfway there, come on!
>> Go, you got it!
>> PROBST: Bob and Randy are
back through the crawl-through
first.
>> Come on! Come on!
>> PROBST: Let's go, girls!
What are you doing?
Fang slowing down.
>> Come on. You got it!
>> PROBST: Bob and Randy with a
bit of a lead for Kota now.
>> Come on! Come on!
>> Hustle! Go! Go!
>> PROBST: Gotta get back to the
mat before the next pair can go.
Corinne and Charlie on the
court.
Kelly and Sugar are losing a
tremendous amount of time for
Fang.
Kelly is dragging.
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: Charlie and Corinne
through the crawl-through.
Ace and Crystal out on the
course for Fang.
>> Come on, baby!
>> PROBST: Kota now at the
second obstacle.
Fang finishing up the first.
>> Let's go.
>> PROBST: Charlie and Corinne
make quick work of it.
Crystal and Ace trying to catch
up.
>> Come on!
Let's go.
Come on!
>> PROBST: Corinne whipping
through the knots for Kota.
>> Get out of the way.
>> PROBST: Corinne has the
second set of flagpole pieces
released.
Ace trying to pick it up for
Fang.
Ace has them undone.
Got to unclip.
>> Do it... oh, that hurt!
It's all right.
>> PROBST: Charlie and Corinne
with a decent lead for Kota.
>> Come on!
>> All right, guys!
20 yards!
>> PROBST: Charlie and Corinne
moving through the crawl.
Ace and Crystal have made up a
lot of time for Fang.
Fang gaining on Kota.
That lead is evaporating now.
Corrine and Charlie are back.
The final two for Kota.
It's Dan and Marcus.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Fang's back.
The final two for Fang:
Matty and Kenny.
Matty throwing himself.
Matty and Kenny quickly through
the crawl-through.
>> Come on, buddy! Come on!
You okay?
Come on.
>> PROBST: Dan and Marcus at the
second obstacle for Kota.
Matty and Kenny right on their
tail.
Dan and Marcus now at the third
obstacle.
Matty and Kenny right there.
They're going to pass Kota now,
climbing over the obstacle.
Matty and Kenny have overtaken
Marcus and Dan!
Fang now in the lead.
Matty and Kenny unbelievable in
this leg.
Kenny has the pieces to the
flagpole down.
Dan has them down.
Matty and Kenny heading back
with the final two pieces to
that flagpole.
Dan and Marcus right behind.
They're going on top of the
challenge.
Fang through first.
Kota right behind.
>> Come on!
Come on!
>> PROBST: Fang still with the
lead on Kota.
We are neck and neck!
Matty and Kenny made up a lot
of time.
Got to get back to the mat.
Then you can start work working
on the flagpole.
Get back, Kenny.
You got to get back!
>> Get up!
>> Come on, Kenny!
>> PROBST: Go!
Gotta untie all six pieces
first.
Then you start working
on assembling it.
>> That's not it!
That's not it!
>> PROBST: This is where
teamwork is going to win or lose
this challenge.
Kota working together very well.
>> Get out of the way!
>> PROBST: Ace not wanting help
from anyone.
After coming so close, Fang now
falling behind.
Ace trying to muscle it in.
All the pieces will interlock.
You don't need to force
anything.
Kota quickly working together
on assembling their flagpole.
>> It's not going in!
>> PROBST: Ace still struggling
to make sense of this.
(cheering)
Kota wins immunity once again!
>> Good job, guys!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Kota, once again,
immunity is yours.
Kota, not much to say.
You continue to dominate
in this game.
Enjoy it.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: And Fang, once again,
Tribal Council, all yours.
And if you continue to play
like individuals, you'll be
there every time.
Tonight, one of the six of you
going home.
You have the afternoon to
figure out who it's going to be.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Ace is a tyrant and a bully
and a lot of people see Ace as
a strong competitor, but he's
been in our tribe for three or
four challenges now, and we
haven't won anything.
So, how is he benefiting me?
♪ ♪
>> The challenge was
challenging.
There were a couple of people
that died right at the end.
I was expecting more from
Kelly, and she really just sort
of petered out.
She goes, it strengthens the
team, and I think she's just
irritating and really dumb.
Kelly's going home tonight.
It would be stupid not to send
her.
>> All right, don't get mad at
me when I say this, but, uh, if
we, if we merge at nine...
>> Yeah.
>> And we go into the last
three ,and it's going to be you,
Sugar or me, she can play the
idol and I can leave, dude.
I think we should flush the
idol tonight.
You and I and her, that's too
much of a risk.
Why can't we play it tonight?
>> Matty, look at me.
She can't play the idol.
Trust me.
>> If it's us three...
>> Trust me.
>> Okay, all right, I trust
you then.
>> Matty wanted to get the idol
out and I just tried to convey
to him that he doesn't really
have to worry about that to that
extent because although I don't
want to tell him I have the
idol; obviously, I do.
Man, don't worry about the idol.
I promise we'll take care of it.
>> All right.
Kelly, then.
>> Kelly.
>> Okay.
>> The alliance is sound.
I would hope to trust Matty.
Sugar I pretty much trust
completely.
I don't see any reason why
Kenny would not go with what it
is, and I think it makes sense
for everyone to get rid of
Kelly.
>> Why not?
>> Because it's not going to
work.
That's what I tried to run by
Ace right when I got here.
>> Why do you trust Ace?
>> Who said I did?
>> Well, then, when you went to
talk to him in the woods, what
did you ask him?
What did he say?
>> He said, "Kelly."
"Kelly."
I said, "I guess.
That sound good to me, dude."
>> I really want Ace out of
here.
>> We can't vote Ace off.
We have to win a freaking
immunity...
>> Have you won one yet since
he's been here?
Okay.
>> I don't know what's going
through Matty's head.
He's running and telling Ace
everything and Ace ain't
running and telling him
anything.
>> Let's just get out Kelly.
I don't know why we have to
get...
Let's just start with this.
>> Okay.
I'm still very leery of Ace and
Sugar because they are in an
alliance, and Kenny, myself,
and Matty, we have to be leery
of everything that's going on
around us.
>> Something is up tonight.
>> Matty...
>> No, no.
>> He's just riding the fence.
>> Right now, the safest best is
to write down Kelly.
>> Ace is probably writing down
Kelly.
Sugar is writing down Kelly.
>> Matty is writing down Kelly.
Right now, I'm really torn
'cause I really want Ace out of
here.
>> Do we trust Ace or Kelly?
I don't trust Ace.
>> I don't trust Ace.
>> Crystal knows something's up,
and she does not trust Matty.
Crystal is on to something.
Right now, know what Crystal
told me?
She told me that, "Yeah, I'm
worried about Matty, that he's
flipping."
And I'm like, "Don't worry.
We're sticking together."
Crystal said, "Okay."
>> All that we have to know is
that Kelly goes next.
That's it.
That's all we have to know
right now.
>> Or blindside Ace.
>> I can't.
I made a promise that I can't
break.
>> Yeah, but, man, you can't
trust someone like that when
they say they have an agreement.
>> We made a serious agreement.
He swore on his mother.
>> You got to think it over.
Matty, like, you just can't take
anybody's word.
In order for you and me to
guarantee to make the merge,
we have to blindside Ace and
then that's a guaranteed merge
for you and me.
I don't trust Ace at all.
I know he's sneaky.
I know he has alliances
back in the Kota tribe.
And Sugar's going to go with Ace
no matter what.
So I was like, I had to talk to
Sugar on a one-on-one basis.
It's weird 'cause his game, you
see people who are really honest
and sweet, kind of get, like,
their heads chopped off by
people like...
>> That's why I connected with
Ace.
>> By people like...
>> Ace.
(laughs)
So I figured, you know, maybe
we could stick together.
>> I know.
I know, huh?
>> I was so shocked today when
Sugar told me that she gave the
hidden immunity idol to Ace.
And I was like, "Wait. What?!"
Since you gave the idol to
Ace, that just shows that you he
is...
>> Well, he didn't ask for it.
I gave it to him.
>> You just gave it to him on
your own will.
>> Yeah.
He didn't, like, talk me out of
it or anything, but I know Ace
is a sneak.
>> Yeah, he's very sleazy.
>> I just wanted to let you
know that they took the idol out
of your bag-- I mean, out of
your jacket-- so you don't think
that somebody else did it.
>> Oh, okay.
>> But I don't think I need to
play it, right?
>> No.
>> You're sure I'm good?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, cool.
>> All right.
>> I told Sugar, "Always keep
the idol with you, you know.
In case something happens."
I just made sure that it's not
in the snake's hands, Ace's
hands and it's back to Sugar's
hands.
>> Uh, the deal with Sugar and
the idol is she has it, and I
think it's quite possible Sugar
thinks "I've used Ace to the
extent that I can."
I'm not particularly worried in
relation to my own regard at the
moment.
I'm going in confident.
That could be the worst thing
possible.
(Probst sighs)
>> PROBST: So, out of ten
challenges, you have won two.
Matty, what is the mood of this
tribe?
>> We're... cursed.
(laughing)
There's something in our water.
There's something in our rice.
But I think we have a curse.
>> PROBST: Kelly, what's your
take on this tribe?
>> Um, we just can't come, like,
as a team, and just, like, work
together.
>> PROBST: I think Kelly hit it
on the head.
What I saw today at the
challenge is a group of people
working as individuals.
>> Jeff, when it came to
putting that flag and pole
together, I really, honestly
felt like Ace wanted to be the
person to put it all together.
"We got to try this."
We got to try this."
I'm like, "We can all piece it
together."
>> PROBST: Ace, do you think
you guys were effective in how
you were working at the end,
trying to put that flag
together?
>> No, we didn't come together
as a group.
And I think I can apportion
definitely a larger percentage
of the blame for how it went
together at the end.
>> PROBST: Crystal, would it
be fair to give Ace a vote,
simply because you thought you
knew how to do it, and you
didn't?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Surprise you, Ace?
>> Nothing surprises me in
Tribal Council, honestly.
>> PROBST: Crystal, you've
been upset at a lot of
challenges.
Tears have come out often.
Do you think it's starting to
have an impact?
>> Oh, definitely.
Some of my tribemates tend to
take it as weakness and will
very well use it against me
tonight.
>> PROBST: Kelly, you're
nodding your head.
>> Um, I never said she was
weak, but when somebody cries,
it's just like, "Why are you
crying?"
Clearly something is, like,
you're just not stable.
>> You don't know where my
tears come from.
Yeah, I'm hurt because we're
losing.
We're not eating.
We're not winning.
And if you don't understand
that, you won't last too much
longer in the game yourself.
>> Okay...
>> And you took me crying one
time as a sign of weakness?
I don't think so.
>> Okay, well, I didn't say that
you were weak, so you can take
what you want.
>> Next question, please.
>> PROBST: Now, Kelly didn't say
you were weak.
Kelly said you were unstable.
>> Yeah, that's worse.
>> She didn't explain to us why
she was crying.
I asked is her afterwards if she
was okay.
She told me...
You don't have to explain.
It's understood.
And sometimes you don't have to
have things written out in black
and white.
I'm not crying over no doggone
danishes, okay?
Really, it gets frustrating,
Kelly; it really does.
We've been down and out from
day one.
But you wouldn't understand it
because you came from a
a winning situation.
>> I'm not banging her down.
Like, I just saw her cry.
That doesn't mean anything.
I wasn't the only one talking
about it.
Ace talked about it...
>> Whoa, before you start to try
and throw people under busses
for no apparent reason, the only
thing I said about Crystal was I
actually understood because
it's frustrating losing over and
over again, just so it drives
you up the wall.
>> PROBST: Kelly, the whole
time Ace was talking, you had a
look on your face like, "Not
true."
>> He is 100% double-talking and
it's just just so annoying, I
just, like, don't even know how
to explain it.
>> Honestly, Kelly, I would
be impressed if you understood
what I was saying half the time.
>> He always has to have the
last word.
It's disgusting.
>> PROBST: Matty, you seem like
one of the few guys tonight who
might have reason to actually
not be worried.
>> There's no sort of semblance
or logic in this tribe, though.
>> PROBST: That must be
maddening when you get to the
vote.
There are so many people,
tonight, it feels like, that
are on the chopping block.
>> It could be any one of us.
It really could be any single
one of us tonight.
>> PROBST: Well, it sounds like
it's going to be an interesting
vote.
It is time to vote.
Ace, you're up.
>> My dear, this has been a
been a long time in the coming.
Hopefully, it happens tonight.
>> Forget you.
Go home.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Kelly.
Crystal.
One vote Kelly;
one vote Crystal.
Kelly.
Two votes Kelly;
one vote Crystal.
Kelly.
That's three votes Kelly;
one vote Crystal.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon: Kelly.
That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Kelly, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, tonight was the first
Tribal Council that I saw some
true passion.
Maybe that's what's been
missing.
Time will tell.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Both tribes are going to vote
somebody out.
>> Susie has made it far
enough in this game.
>> Blindside Ace.
>> Take Marcus out.
>> Kenny, Crystal, and I vote
for Sugar.
>> I think it's going to be
Dan.
>> Crystal thinks Kenny's
out; Kenny thinks Crystal's out;
and you're voting Crystal, and
you're voting Crystal, and Matty
is voting Crystal.
>> Okay.
>> I was actually going to vote
you.
>> I voted for Crystal because,
you know what?
She doesn't really have the
power to push a team when she's
the one quitting half the
challenges.
I think the Fang tribe is still
cursed.
I think they're still going to
go down.
They need to work together.
Maybe tonight's Tribal Council,
they'll communicate better,
but I definitely wanted to stay
in the game, but, you know,
if it's my time to go,
it's my time to go.