>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
The Kota tribe has enjoyed
the benefits of winning a
staggering nine out of 11
challenges against the rapidly
dwindling Fang tribe, but on day
21 both tribes competed for
individual immunity.
Ace in the water first!
Marcus wins individual immunity!
And both tribes were sent to
Tribal Council.
At the Kota Tribal Council,
Susie dissed Corinne...
>> I think I'm stronger than
Corinne.
>> PROBST: Corinne not buying
that at all.
...and narrowly avoided
getting voted out.
We're tied, three votes Susie,
three votes Dan, one vote left.
That honor went to Dan.
The tribe has spoken.
At the Fang Tribal Council,
Sugar surprised everyone by
stabbing her closest ally in
the back.
With physical force Ace out of
the game, Fang needs a miracle
to turn things around.
Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> What's so funny?
>> How was that compared to the
other Tribal Councils you had?
>> Uh, the other ones are easy.
(laughter)
That wasn't meant to be funny.
>> No. Yeah, it was tough.
>> Yeah, I mean, I didn't say it
to get people to laugh.
Tonight was not fun.
That was my friend that left.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, think about what I
say before you just instantly
start laughing, 'cause not all
the time I'm trying to be funny.
We voted Dan off tonight.
Uh, the vote was 4-3.
I voted for Susie just in case
Dan had the hidden immunity
idol and could have taken
anybody he wanted out.
He was my friend, but he had to
go.
>> I would like to analyze
what our weaknesses are and
shore 'em up.
Because I personally feel like
the merge is coming in the next
couple days.
>> Well, and the way I look at
it, operation clean sweep;
these six mowing down that four.
You know, this is the heart of
who's left, the six of us.
>> Let's do it.
>> We can make it happen.
>> We can't, like... I mean,
I'm not trying to call you out,
particularly Susie, but like you
can't threaten to vote for
Corinne and not tell somebody
that there is a problem there.
>> Yeah. When you and I had the
conversation and you said I
wasn't helpful around camp,
you know, I understood that.
I'm sensitive to it now.
But what I don't understand is
during Tribal you had, like, a
lot of other gripes.
Prior to going in, Susie told
me that she was gonna vote for
me based on the fact that she
did not think I did enough work
around camp.
Well, then we get to Tribal.
Who's the weakest player in the
game?
I think Corinne's weaker
than me.
I think I swim better than
Corinne, I think I have
better upper-body strength.
The woman is 47 years old.
What could she possibly have
over me?
Look, I'm not really sure that
you're not going to vote me out
as soon as you get your next
opportunity, and I don't want to
feel that way about somebody who
I'm planning on going to
the final six with.
>> I guess what we're
wondering is...
>> Will I sell you out sooner?
Is that what you're asking me?
>> Yeah, basically.
>> No. Right now they have me in
their alliance of six.
They may think they have all
the power, but I'm feeling like
my goal is that I have the
power.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(man groans)
>> How gnarly was that, dude?
>> We can make a fire and...
>> That was crazy.
>> Sorry to surprise you like
that.
>> No worries.
>> That was a textbook blindside
to Ace.
So I'm so glad that I stuck to
my promise and didn't vote him
out.
But I'm not gonna corner
myself with any pacts on my
girlfriend again.
Ace told me he had you in his
back pocket, like you guys are
friends, buddy buddy.
>> Yeah, that's exactly what he
thought.
>> As far as I know, Ace was
totally like your...
>> He was playing you, Matty.
>> Okay, well, he was playing
you.
>> I trust Kenny a lot more
than I trust Ace.
And Kenny's completely honest
with me and told me that Ace
has been trying to throw me
under the bus, so I figured I'd
better take him out as soon as
I can.
>> You're gonna be gunning
for me now, Crystal.
>> No, she's not.
>> Dude, that is... that's done.
I mean, I'm looking at you in
the whatever light we have,
Matty.
If you want to start from a
clean slate, we can.
>> Don't let anybody else...
>> Yeah, don't let anybody else
get in your head.
>> I'm a little concerned that
Crystal's upset with me,
because I voted for Crystal.
I had no options.
I-I couldn't break that promise
to Ace.
I'm just praying for a merge
and I'm praying for this game
to change and if it doesn't,
I'm in deep trouble.
>> Guys, I have a plan for the
merge tomorrow.
>> I hope there's a merge.
>> We are going to be the final
four, us four right here.
Sugar does have the idol.
>> You guys cannot tell them
that I still have it.
>> Yeah, okay.
>> Nobody will know you have
the idol.
>> Cool. We're good.
We're starting over.
>> Hopes are high right now for
the current Fang members, and if
there's going to be a merge,
hopefully we can outwit,
outlast and outplay the current
remaining Kota members so that
we can go as far as possible.
>> You guys are all survivors.
>> Welcome to the game.
(laughs)
(growling)
>> Not only did I go above and
beyond to be extra nice to
Susie, I understood that she
thought I didn't do much
around camp.
Then we got to Tribal and she,
like, whips out all
this other stuff.
I was, like, highly annoyed with
it.
>> Uh-oh.
>> Oh... Ooh.
Oh, it's a spoon.
After what Susie said at last
night's Tribal, I plan on
burying her as soon as possible,
alive.
I am an extremely vindictive
person, and I will get my
revenge.
>> Here they come.
>> Tree mail.
"For a feast that will be
catered and enjoyed under the
sun, it's time to party on the
equator like a beach bash, so
have some fun."
>> Wait, there's more.
"Take only your personal
possessions.
All you need awaits
your arrival, a brand-new
tribe, a brand-new game, a
new way of survival."
>> Whoo!
>> Is this my personal
possession?
>> This is mine.
>> We got a beach, and there's
food!
>> Tree mail's got "merge"
written all over it.
It's talking about a feast.
It's talking about fun, and most
importantly it's talking about
moving to the beach.
>> We're going to the equator.
>> All I want to say is Kota
six, and that's all that needs
to be said on that.
And don't be fooled.
New tribe of the ten of us
remaining, Kota Six to the end,
Fang four, good-bye.
>> Oh, wow!
>> Oh, my God!
>> There's mixed nuts!
>> Oh!
>> Hi!
>> My heart was pounding
'cause I couldn't tell you the
feeling that seeing an endless
amount of food.
It was, like, it was so nice.
It was so nice.
It was unforgettable.
It says "Open only after you
have finished enjoying your
feast, as once this box is
opened, the feast is over."
>> We're not opening that until
this is depleted.
>> Guys, we're gonna be here
all afternoon.
The meatloaf?
>> I gotta remember to swallow.
>> Stay away from the box.
>> There's a big box that says,
"Do not open until everybody's
done eating."
And I don't know what's in the
box.
I know whatever it is it ends
the fun and it starts the game
play again, and I am going to
prolong that as long as I can.
>> This meatloaf tastes so good!
>> Chow down!
>> Kenny, no need to speak,
just eat, dude.
>> Oh, sweet.
>> Does anyone want me to pour
them a glass of white wine?
>> Matty, could you hook me up?
>> I would love red wine.
>> There's, like, juice.
>> There's two bottles of wine
right there.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I saw the hidden immunity
idol note under the table.
And the idol was more
tempting than the food.
>> What's that clue...? Is that
something you guys brought?
>> Yeah, let's see what it says.
>> I was trying to read it to
see what it was.
And by then Charlie already
looked over and started reading
it, too.
>> Read it out loud.
>> And then, I read it and it
said "You can either share it or
keep it to yourself."
And I wanted to keep it to
myself.
>> Put it down until we eat.
Just-just cover it and we'll
read it...
>> I want to eat.
>> Let's live in the moment
right now.
>> And then I was like, "Okay, I
guess my cover is blown."
>> Guys, I feel bad not sharing
this because I saw the whole
thing.
So I feel like you guys should
take a look, too.
>> What does it say?
>> It's about the immunity idol.
>> Damn it, damn it, there's my
chance to find the hidden
immunity idol for myself, and
Charlie blew it for me.
>> "You have just discovered a
clue to another hidden immunity
idol.
You can keep it a secret or
share.
Either way, you must find it
before your day at the beach is
over.
On the sand lies a large dead
log cradled in the crook of a
tree.
Beneath the end of the tree's
lowest limb you can dig for
immunity."
>> Who wants it? I see it.
>> It's whoever decides to get
up and finish eating.
>> It's right over my right
shoulder.
>> I like that idea. I would...
>> That's a good idea.
>> It occurred to me that if
everyone's gonna act so casual
about not really wanting an
immunity idol that's hidden just
a few feet away from the table,
then fine, I'll call all of your
bluffs... and I will force you
to get rid of it.
What do you say we find it and,
as a group, set it sail?
>> Yeah, yeah, set it free.
>> That's a great idea.
>> We don't need no stinkin'
idol.
>> Randy caught my drift
immediately and became the
champion of this idea.
>> Anybody opposed to finding
the idol and setting it adrift?
Sending it to the ocean gods?
>> I think that'd be cool.
>> Let's go.
>> All right.
>> I'm gonna start off
shirtless-- if we get naked,
then so be it.
I didn't even need to see a
note.
I knew that the weird-shaped
tree on the beach was
significant.
It was, like, pointing into the
sand, and I'm, like, "How
obvious."
>> What about over there?
>> I told you I would in less
than a minute, and it took two
seconds.
>> Yeah, Randy!
>> I'm sorry if I'm sounding
arrogant, but it was a joke.
I gave myself 20 seconds.
I think I took seven.
I'm king of Gabon.
>> That's your boasting rights,
my friend.
>> That's right.
>> I'll say it loud and proud.
Congratulations for your quick
wit and mind.
>> I found it, and, uh, I don't
want it, and if anybody else
wants it, by all means, take it.
>> You touch that, it's "good
game" for you.
Immunity-- the most important
thing in this game.
But if I were to take it, then
I'd look like a snake.
I can't take that chance.
>> It's the apple in the Garden
of Eden.
>> Yeah, you want the apple,
take it, but... no.
>> You want the apple, Matty.
>> Crystal?
>> No, don't touch it, dawg.
>> Don't touch it.
>> I wanted that immunity idol.
I'm not even gonna sit here and
lie.
I wanted that immunity idol,
because that's pretty much your
protection in the game.
>> It was the apple in Eden, and
that idol represented the apple
in Eden, and if you grab that
idol, you are biting into the
apple and you'd be exiled from
Eden.
>> Matty, you're thinking too
long.
>> I'm not gonna do it.
And nobody wants to be thrown
out of Eden.
(several talking at once)
>> Just to tie it to the...
>> You sure?
>> Yeah, 'cause of the sand.
>> All right, guys, all of us to
the beach.
>> With all due respect to
President Bongo, I am the new
king of Gabon.
I'm sorry, but I rule.
This ocean, it's mine.
One last time-- anybody who
wants immunity, it's theirs.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Who wants it?
>> The ocean wants it.
>> The ocean!
All those Fang, Kota members,
they work for me.
I'm king. Cheers.
(whooping)
>> These people are so stupid.
I got ten people to throw an
immunity idol into the ocean.
It's never been done.
It was a perfect way to make the
situation much easier for the
Kota Six to gain control of the
game, because there's no extra
idol floating around to really
screw up any votes.
>> Throwing the immunity idol
out to sea, yeah, it was a
beautiful, lovely thought and
everything, but that is a very
prized possession in this game,
and luckily, I have one.
(laughter)
>> You guys want me to read it?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, it's open.
>> It says: "Note number one."
>> "Note number one."
>> Here we go.
>> "In this bag, there are ten
numbered stones.
Without looking, each tribe
member will grab a stone.
When you are finished, read
number two."
>> Okay.
>> All right.
>> "Note number two."
>> "Congratulations, you have
just divided yourself into two
new tribes."
>> I thought there were gonna be
ten new buffs in the box and
that we were gonna be a merged
tribe.
I just never in a million
years... predicted.
>> "The odd numbers are the new
Fang Tribe.
The even numbers are the new
Kota Tribe."
>> Not again! (chuckles)
Damn! (sighs)
>> "Open the bag, collect your
new buffs, and immediately
return to your respective camps.
The game has changed once
again."
>> I knew that was gonna happen.
>> "Enjoy the adventure."
The new Kota Tribe is Bob and
Marcus, Susie, Crystal and
Kenny.
I missed you once, I'll miss
you again.
I'll see you in a day or two.
The new Fang Tribe: myself,
Charlie and Corinne, and then
we've got Matty and Sugar.
Charlie and Corinne and myself
have a deal, so... we're safe.
Uh, I am worried about Marcus.
I just don't trust Susie.
Susie's crazy and Susie's
stupid, and that's a horrible
combination.
>> Are you going?
>> Yeah. See you in a day or
two.
>> We actually got lucky, and
there is a majority of the Kota
six in each of the two tribes.
I don't need the immunity idol.
I have great relationships in
this game.
And that's honestly what I'm
banking on.
Because I know, at the end of
the day, that no immunity idol
gets me to the finals.
>> Are you here with us, or are
you leaving?
>> I feel like I have a lot more
power right now, because I
really can, if I want to,
swing... with Kenny and Crystal
and take the power away from
Marcus and Bob.
>> I'm still... the enemy.
Even though I have on a yellow
bandana, I don't feel very
hopeful right now as far as me
lasting in this game if I'm
gonna be on the shorter end of
the stick.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Welcome home.
>> Thank you.
>> Yes. This is it.
>> You ready to do this?
>> Are you ready to do this?
>> I'm ready to do this.
>> It's Kota.
>> 'Cause you know what this
means, right?
>> Yeah, this is...
This is us, Bob.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> Everybody thought it was
gonna be the merge, but now I'm
Kota.
Over here, all I have is
Crystal.
I feel like I don't have
numbers, and I feel like, you
know, I might be the next to go,
but hopefully, that's not the
case.
>> I know, that's so cool.
>> Yes, he is.
>> One of my best friends from
Atlanta is her cousin.
>> Yeah. 'Cause we were just
talking, and he was just, like,
"Yeah, you may not know this guy
named Kenny. Kenny Cox."
>> And she's, like, "Actually,
yeah..."
>> "Yeah, that's my cousin."
(laughs)
>> It's a small world.
>> That's insane.
>> I come to find out that
Crystal is the cousin of one of
my best friends.
It's a really strange situation,
because I feel... a little torn.
I'm in a situation where I have
completely calculated voting her
out.
But, you know, since we changed
tribes, I don't know if that's
still the case.
If you're anything like your
cousin, I mean, then I know...
I know you're good people,
and-and I just... I just want to
keep good people around, but...
>> That's, that's how I am.
I think that was Kenny's
concern, too.
>> Crystal is actually a really
cool girl.
This is a person I can be
straight-up with.
This is a person I can talk to.
This is me crumpling up my
playbook, throwing it out the
window.
>> I'm telling you, this is my
word.
>> Yeah.
>> In the unlikely event we have
to go to Tribal, I'm not writing
your name down.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm not writing Kenny's name
down.
I'm not writing Bob's name down.
>> Yeah. I'm...
>> I'm telling you that right
now.
Marcus and I now have a link,
and hopefully, I can use that
link to my advantage.
But me telling Marcus that I
won't write his name down,
that's me playing the game.
Because I also told Ace I would
not write his name down, and Ace
got blindsided.
(trumpeting)
>> Welcome to Fang, everybody.
>> Thanks.
>> That was a surprise, huh?
>> Oh, my God.
I knew that kind of crap was
gonna happen.
>> Yeah?
>> I didn't want to believe it.
>> The Kota Six, before the
switch-up, decided that we were
all gonna stick together going
into the hypothetical merge.
But now we've been split up into
two tribes...
The Kota Six, luckily, were
up three-two in both of the
tribes.
So we can still execute our plan
and stay together, Kota Six.
So I need to make sure that here
at Fang, Corinne, Randy and I
stick together as the previous
members of the Kota Tribe.
>> Oh.
>> It's good to see you, man.
>> You, too.
>> It's suicide.
I mean, if she has the idol...
The only thing we can say is we
can tell Matty we're voting for
Sugar, Sugar we're voting for
Matty, and then hope that if she
has the idol, Matty goes.
>> If I were to vote tomorrow, I
would vote for Matty.
He doesn't have a hidden
immunity idol and he's too much
of a threat for me in individual
immunity, and he's threatening
to Marcus and Marcus is my
alliance.
So he will go home as soon as we
vote.
>> How do you get along with
Corinne and Charlie?
>> Awesome.
My first gay friend.
>> What about Corinne?
>> She's-she's cool, too.
>> Randy is a great dude, I love
having him around, but I don't
trust him.
He went to Kota, he found a
home at Kota, and that's his new
family.
I'm not too unpleased that
Ace got voted out, because I
didn't have to do it, I didn't
have to break my promise.
>> Uh-huh.
>> But it upset me, because you
just went along with Crystal
like that.
>> I thought I was going along
with Kenny, 'cause Kenny was
being honest with me.
>> No, Kenny didn't trust Ace.
>> Wow...!
>> Y-Y-You...
>> I know. I know.
>> Ace was covering you the
whole time.
He never was gunning for you.
Ever.
>> Now I believe that.
>> And he might have gunned for
you later, but he wasn't gunning
for you now.
>> I didn't know.
I think Kenny and Crystal duped
me.
I feel awful that I got rid of
Ace.
I feel so bad.
I wish I could apologize to Ace.
I think I may have made a big
mistake, and I feel really bad.
I believe you.
Thank you.
We have to, I guess.
>> There's nothing else to do.
It's just you or I.
>> You're right.
>> We have to keep our eyes and
ears open.
So, if I hear that you're going
to be voted out...
>> Yeah?
>> You've got to use the idol.
>> I know.
>> If you're gonna hear that I'm
going to get voted out, you
gotta tell me so I can try to
maneuver something.
Me and Sugar have each other's
back and she has the idol.
So, I think we can help each
other.
>> Were you trying to bring this
back?
>> Yeah, I have.
I've brought some big logs back.
I just...
I might have to break this up.
Hey, you know what?
It might be easier to pull it
up that way and then take it
out.
>> We have a powerful pact to
get us to the final six without
even batting an eyelash.
The way things divided up is
perfect.
>> And theoretically, like,
nothing should change.
Bob gives me a lot of
confidence that he's not going
to budge on the situation.
But Susie always made me a bit
nervous.
I think, given the opportunity,
she would sell me down the
river in a second.
>> We have numbers on both
sides, kind of, right now.
Let's say for some reason we
lost.
I can make a decision to go one
way or the other.
>> I am far more paranoid than
I have been in this game.
Kenny and Crystal are super
tight and Bob and I are super
tight here and Susie's in the
middle, spinning around in
circles, playing dizzy bat.
And where is she going to stop?
I have no idea.
>> We can make it to the top
six. That's our goal, right?
>> Yeah.
But then, when we're there,
where does that put me, then?
'Cause I am one of the weaker
people. Is that gonna...
Am I always going to be sixth?
Because think about it.
It's one thing to be in the top
six, but I need to be in the
top three.
Marcus is basically the king,
but I have the power right now
to just cut his head off.
If I do switch, it's his own
fault because he didn't give me
a clear statement.
(snorting)
>> We got mail!
>> I just think...
Can you imagine a better...
I mean, three and three?
>> It's perfect.
>> My only concern is that that
crazy bitch Susie could flip to
get rid of Bob and Marcus.
>> And that is a "save Marcus"
move more than anything.
And then, then it doesn't really
matter what crazy Susie does.
>> Right.
I was very pleased with the
conversation I had with Randy
this morning just regarding
Matty, because we need to get
rid of him first if we have to
go to Tribal, and, like, he
totally is on board.
100%.
>> If we have to go, as much as
I'd hate to do it, we'd have to
take out Matty.
>> Yeah.
>> Just because of the idol.
There is a one in a billion
chance that Sugar is, like, a
rocket scientist and she's
hiding the idol.
I'd like to see Matty stay
around, but keeping Charlie and
Corinne happy is more important
than keeping Matty happy.
>> Hey, we got mail!
"If you can't keep it up, there
is reason to worry.
You may be the first to join
the jury."
>> If we can't keep it up? Up.
Something in the air.
>> You've seen the challenges
where your wrist is like
strapped to a huge bucket of
water?
>> Oh!
>> At this point in the game,
I'm very concerned about my
time here, and I don't know how
much I have left.
Every moment seems to be pretty
valuable.
So today I'm going to give it
my all.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How you guys doing?
>> Great.
>> Good.
>> PROBST: Marcus, are you
starting to think maybe you
don't have this game completely
figured out?
>> Uh, yeah, I threw away my
game plan the minute I saw that
box open up and reached in and
pulled a number out.
>> PROBST: Corinne, happy with
the new tribe division?
>> You know, I've been Kota for
a really long time.
I still feel like Kota.
In fact, we're not calling it
"Fang."
We're calling it "Fayng," just
'cause "Fang" has such a bad
connotation.
>> PROBST: Matty, as the only
true remaining Fang member,
is it hard to hear Corinne
say, "We don't even say 'Fang'
'cause that's tainted."
>> I'm trapped in the
ghetto, man-- I can't get out of
the ghetto, so whatever you want
to call it, I don't care.
"Fang," "Fayng," I just want to
get out of there one day.
(Corinne laughing)
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
Today's challenge, very simple
in concept, much more difficult
to execute.
With your arms outstretched,
you will use the tops of your
hands to hold two polls against
an overhead board.
If you lower your arms even
slightly, you'll release the
pressure on the polls, the
polls will drop.
When a poll drops, you're out
of the challenge.
The last person left standing
wins immunity for their entire
tribe, keeps the entire tribe
safe from Tribal Council.
To put it another way, the
first tribe to lose all their
members from this challenge
goes to Tribal Council.
Somebody will be voted out.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Each of you has an
individual station that has
been adjusted based on your
height, so everything is fair.
Take a spot at your station.
We'll get started.
Everybody feel good?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Okay.
This challenge is officially
underway.
And after one second, Crystal
is out.
Last person left in this
challenge wins immunity for
their entire tribe.
You will be a hero.
Sugar is out after ten seconds.
This is all about mind over
matter.
It is going to hurt and it's
going to hurt quickly.
24 days you've been out here
living on very little.
Not much sleep.
A lot of mental pressure.
Susie's out of the challenge
for Kota.
Kota now down to three members
left.
Randy's starting to shake a bit.
Randy's out of the challenge,
and Corinne is out of the
challenge.
Two more Fang members drop at
the same time.
Fang now down to two people
left.
Kenny drops the pole.
Kenny is out of the challenge
for Kota.
Very quickly, this is coming
down to a showdown.
Bob and Marcus left for Kota.
Charlie and Matty left for Fang.
Marcus starting to shake a
little bit, going to have to
dig deep, find somewhere else
to go.
Change arm position.
Marcus drops the pole.
He's out of the challenge.
Kota down to their last member.
The oldest person in this game,
Bob, fighting to hold on to
Tribal immunity for Kota, while
Matty and Charlie fight for
Fang.
Bob drops his poles, Kota goes
to Tribal Council, somebody
going home.
Charlie struggling to hang on.
Charlie is out.
We have a showdown.
Matty, the last Fang member
remaining and Bob, the last Kota
member remaining.
>> Ain't no thing, Bobby Boy.
>> PROBST: Do not get foolish.
Don't lose your concentration.
Don't start listening to
anybody, including me.
All it takes is a moment's
lapse in your concentration and
you're out of this challenge.
That's it.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: Block it out.
>> Matty's going to drop.
He's going to drop.
Matty's been shaking for a
while, Bob, stick it up.
(Matty laughs)
>> PROBST: Matty's going
to be laughing his way right to
Tribal Council.
That pole is right on the
edge.
Both poles on the edge of the
board for Matty.
You need to stop jabbering and
start concentrating.
>> You've got this, Bob.
>> PROBST: Matty has less than
a quarter of an inch hanging on
to the edge of that board.
If it slips off, it will fall.
It's over for Fang.
Bob hanging in there for Kota.
Matty fighting.
That pole is right on the edge.
>> Hold on, Bob. Hold on, Bob.
>> PROBST: Trying to work it
back now.
Bob hanging in there for Kota.
Matty flirting with disaster.
Bob drops his pole!
Matty wins immunity for the
Fang tribe.
>> Way to go, man.
I couldn't do it.
>> Good job, Bob.
>> PROBST: Matty,
congratulations.
Not only do you keep yourself
safe, you keep your entire
tribe safe.
Nice job.
Matty single-handedly wins
immunity for the Fang tribe.
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> It's "Fayng."
>> PROBST: Don't forget your
tribe flag, Fayng.
>> It was good to win, but it
really didn't matter.
In fact, if we had lost, I'm
absolutely sure that Matty
would have been going home.
>> I'm pretty happy with myself
right now that I, uh, I managed
to pull that off.
Now the curiosity is killing me.
What's going to happen in Kota,
'cause it's totally up in the
air.
>> PROBST: Kota, not such good
news for you.
Tribal Council tonight where
one of the five of you will be
voted out.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> I would like to see either
Kenny or Crystal go home.
The big question for me is can
I get to the final three by
trusting Marcus?
We'll see where this is going
to get me.
I've got to get to that top
three, I have to.
>> We just got back from our
first challenge as Kota Part
Three, and it was a less than
ideal result.
>> You did awesome.
>> I really looked up to you.
>> Yeah.
>> You did really great.
>> Oh, wow.
>> I didn't even get one second
out of it, 'cause it just
wasn't... it didn't fit right.
>> Once they tilted it in I'm
like, damn it.
>> That was a tough one, for
sure.
Unfortunately, either Kenny
or Crystal is going to have to
go home tonight.
I would prefer to have Ken go
home tonight, just because
Crystal and I have a reasonably
good relationship at this point.
Let me tell you what I was
thinking-- and I need you to be
super honest if you can do it or
not-- would be, like, I hate to
say it, but like, if Ken goes
home tonight then we're good.
And then that gives us a shoe in
for who goes next.
Like, it's obviously going to
be Susie.
That's, that's a no-brainer
for me.
But the hope is that you're now
part of the Kota Six, instead of
Susie. It just...
>> Well, can you sell 'em on it?
>> Yeah, because Corinne can't
stand Susie.
Randy, you know can't stand
Susie and frankly, Crystal,
the benefit of you screwing up
in challenges is that...
>> Right now, I am batting zero.
>> I hate to do this.
>> Marcus and I now have a
solid relationship, but when you
start talking about knocking
off my number-one ally just so
you can get further in the
game, I'm not pleased. At all.
>> I know you told me yesterday
you weren't writing my name
down.
>> No.
>> I'm telling you that I'm not
writing your name down tonight.
>> Marcus is playing the nice
guy, but he's a schemer.
I'm playing nice girl, liar
and schemer.
The game is outwit, outlast and
you can't outwit Crystal Cox,
baby.
>> I'm thinking that the least
threatening person is Crystal.
She's not going to beat us.
I mean, she has not run faster,
she cannot swim, she can't
balance.
She can't even do the hand
thing.
>> Yeah, she had a hard time
with that.
>> So, let's minimize our risk
of somebody getting immunity.
>> I said we should take
Crystal out first because she
may do better now that she's
eating.
>> Yeah, but you...
>> But then at the same time...
>> Bob beat her, I beat her...
Like, she couldn't even hold--
You beat her. She's atrocious.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> My thought was tonight Ken
and then hopefully we don't
have to go for a while but then
Crystal would be next.
>> Marcus has a lot of control
of who should be voted off and
Bob's just going to follow
whatever he says.
I feel safer at this point
to stay with Marcus in which
way we're going to vote.
Right now I'm actually putting
trust in you, and that's huge.
>> I thought we've been doing
that for a while at this point.
>> Yeah, I know.
And my guarantee is that you
will help me get there.
>> Once we get there, let's say
that you got Matty and Randy
there.
>> Then it's just...
But everybody knows Matty's a
threat so, Matty's gonna go
first and then Randy and Bob
and then Corinne...
>> I'm good with that.
>> So, that makes the most
sense.
>> Okay.
>> I feel like I can use Marcus
to get me at least to the top
three so I have a chance at one.
That's how I look at it.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
Susie will either go with us or
she gets voted off tonight.
That's... that's...
What do you mean no?
What do you mean?
>> Really?
>> Yes.
I can't let them do it.
>> Marcus told you that he
wanted to write my name down?
>> Yes.
And I'm not writing your name,
Kenny.
>> Kenny being safe tonight is
riding 100% on Sue.
Or else Kenny goes home.
>> Did you clean the fish, Bob?
>> What's that?
>> You clean the fish?
>> Yeah, I got it all right.
>> Almost ready to eat.
>> I don't feel super
comfortable if I was to vote
with Crystal and Kenny and
vote off Marcus.
'Cause I don't know if Crystal
and Kenny could help me get to
the top three.
>> Susie, Susie...
Okay?
>> Okay.
I have a huge decision to
make tonight in which way to go.
Either Marcus or Bob or I can
vote with Kenny and Crystal.
I don't know if it's good or
bad.
I'm confused and I just don't
know.
I don't know how to feel about
it right now.
It's scary and that's the truth.
>> PROBST: So, Crystal, you and
Kenny had not spent any time
with Kota.
What's it like?
>> To me, the Kota camp is like
corporate espionage.
You wear the suit, but what's
going on in your head?
Whereas at Fang, this is the
projects, I'm eating some rice,
we're hungry, let's go to war.
And over there it's like "I wear
my suit."
>> PROBST: So, Bob, now that a
merge maybe isn't around the
corner, does it change your
strategy?
>> Yes.
Last time I was here one of the
reasons I made the decision I
made was I thought a merge was
imminent.
I made a mistake.
>> PROBST: So, you're saying you
regret your last vote?
>> Had I known it was going to
go this way, yes, I might have
done something differently.
>> PROBST: So, Marcus, is it
important to keep this tribe
physically strong to win
challenges or that I hang on to
this alliance and hope that a
merge is coming?
>> I think it's important to
keep the tribe physically
strong and ready for challenges.
My hope is to keep us as strong
as we can.
>> I think that's total bull,
what he just said in his mouth.
He's definitely looking for a
merge around the corner and
have numbers to take out Fang.
Is it not a strategy, Marcus,
to vote out Fang?
>> You know very well that we
beat you guys seven times in a
row and why would we want to
change any of the people in
there?
Frankly, I think you're really
a nice guy and it sucks
that your frustration is being
taken out in this direction, you
know?
>> But I feel that you are the
leader of Kota and that you
are the special Kota guy that
everybody's listening to to
vote somebody off.
>> I'm one of the five opinions
here and we don't see who we
vote for until the final vote
is called, so...
>> PROBST: So, Bob, getting to
the vote, is it clear-cut?
>> Uh, yes.
Yeah.
>> PROBST: Susie, is this an
easy decision for you tonight?
>> I've made my decision and
I'm okay with it.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to get to the vote.
Marcus, you're up.
>> Ken, sorry, buddy, it's just
that it's time.
>> You are not the Kota god.
Good-bye.
>> Sorry, Ken.
However, spilling your guts
tonight makes it a little bit
easier.
>> You like comics when the
little guy takes out the big guy
or the bully?
Well, hopefully that happens
tonight.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Marcus.
Kenny.
One vote Marcus, one vote Kenny.
Two votes Kenny, one vote
Marcus.
We're tied.
Two votes Marcus, two votes
Kenny.
One vote left.
Ninth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon and the first
member of our jury...
Marcus.
You need to bring me your torch.
Marcus, the tribe has spoken.
Just when you think you're
in control of this game,
blindside.
Grab your torches, head back
to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
Meet the new Fayng.
>> Just set it forward and drop
it, please.
>> Shh!
>> Right now, just drop it.
>> PROBST: Same as the old Fang.
Fayng, one big happy tribe,
obviously.
And at Kota, Kenny is the man
of the house.
>> Right now I know for a fact
that I can win this game.
>> I see the future of Kota
Part Three as being probably a
very sneaky one.
I mean, talk about corporate
espionage.
I feel bad for Bob.
I don't see him necessarily
surviving the next few days.
You know, obviously the people
that wrote my name down get to
see me in the future.
And, you know, I forgive, but I