>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
18 castaways were cut off from
the world by miles of empty
savannah and endless jungles
filled with wild creatures.
But the fiercest predator in
Gabon was the yellow tribe...
Kota wins immunity and reward!
...who systematically devoured
the weak and struggling red
tribe Fang.
>> It's tough having to deal
with the losses over and over
again.
It starts to make you feel like
you might not ever win.
>> PROBST: We are picking new
tribes.
>> What?!
>> No, no, no.
>> PROBST: On day ten, a tribe
swap gave Fang the opportunity
to improve themselves.
>> I'm going to go with Kelly.
>> PROBST: But they continued
to be their own worst enemy by
foolishly picking weak players
over stronger ones.
That may be the most surprising
decision in ten days out here.
At the end of the tribe swap,
Sugar, the pinup model, wasn't
chosen and was sent on her
second trip to Exile Island.
>> I already have the idol, so
I chose comfort.
(chuckles)
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, former Fang member
Randy, the wedding
videographer...
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Randy scores for
Kota!
...made every point in a 3-0
blowout of his old tribe.
Kota wins immunity!
By day 12, Fang had hit an
all-time low.
>> It was like we were legless
chickens racing against sleek
weasels.
>> PROBST: And faced with the
choice to vote out a strong
member-- Jacquie-- or a weak
one-- Kelly-- they acted as
though they had a death wish and
weakened their tribe yet again.
Jacquie, the tribe has spoken.
And Ace lost one of his closest
allies.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> The whole tribal thing is a
trip.
>> Uh, sure.
>> Is she here?
>> No, but she's coming.
>> Right now?
>> Uh, Tribal didn't pan out the
way I expected.
Jacquie got the boot, and now
I'm sort of sitting a little
high and dry.
>> No.
>> I think they were scared
about me having any strength in
my alliance with Jacquie.
Maybe now I will be able to
pull off some sort of coup de
grace once again with, uh,
Sugar.
She's back from Exile Island.
One of Sugar's biggest pluses
is the fact that she has the
immunity idol tucked up her
sleeve, and I've got Sugar in
my pocket.
>> Hey.
>> Hi.
Hello.
>> Welcome back.
>> Yeah.
So that means Jacquie's gone.
>> Yep.
>> That sucks.
My very first thought when I
saw that it was the new Fang
tribe was, "Yay, I get to see
Jacquie and Ace."
But instead, I saw Kelly, and
that was a big surprise.
I hate Tribal Council.
Luckily, it was dark, so maybe
I could have hidden some of my
disappointment.
>> Is Exile Island, uh, cool?
>> It was this time.
>> It's a cool place?
It was inside the Sugar Shack.
>> Yeah, it's not bad.
>> So the clue was pretty hard
to find, huh, for the idol?
>> Uh, I-I don't know.
I gave up after three clues the
first time, so...
>> It's called the Sugar Shack
now.
(chuckles)
>> Sugar, Sugar, Sugar.
She's been out to Exile Island
the longest.
She's had plenty of time to
look for the idol.
And I feel in my heart she has
the idol.
So I got to get rid of her.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> Oh, yeah, yeah.
There's another guy down there.
Oh, there's, like, two, three,
dude.
>> Oh, my God.
We're eating this morning.
>> All right!
>> I think we have, like, four
really good-sized tilapia in
here.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Yay!
>> Look how big that one is.
>> So many fish.
>> Ow!
That guy right there.
>> It'll shock you if you
touch him.
>> Grab a hold of him.
>> Oh, damn, you're right!
In addition to the gill net,
Bob checked the traps, and he
had a shocking surprise, which
was literal.
It was this little fish.
He's about four inches long.
And every time you pick him
up, he sends a little electric
charge through your hand.
>> Ooh, he can-- I felt it
through my fingers.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> That was weird.
>> Randy.
>> Dude, we got five.
>> We have five, like...
>> Look how big they are.
>> Huge fish.
>> Good-sized tilapia.
>> It's unbelievable.
Man, that's a nice drag.
>> Yeah, that was a big one.
>> Dan, myself, and Susie, uh,
got picked to be in this new
Kota tribe.
It's-it's wonderful.
I can't believe it.
Gill net worked-- unreal.
Fish, beans, corn.
Way, way better than Fang.
So I have no complaints.
Beautiful.
Kota welcomed the three Fang
members very, very fast into the
tribe, but if they had to vote
somebody out right now, they'd
vote the old Fang people out.
But, uh, you know, I'll work on
them.
When they say to adapt, they
mean to adapt, and this crusty
old man can do it.
(elephants trumpeting)
(trumpeting)
(deep growling breaths)
>> (whispers): Hey, hey, hey,
hey, everybody, everybody.
Everybody come here.
Everybody come here...
Be quiet.
>> It's an elephant, huh?
>> Right there.
Right there.
Right at the bottom.
There he is.
See him?
(elephant trumpeting)
>> Whoa.
>> That is so cool.
>> Look how big his tusks are.
>> I know.
That's crazy.
They could be, like, right in
our camp, and we wouldn't be
able to see them at nighttime.
>> Looks crazy.
(elephant trumpeting)
Oh, here, he's gonna rip
something.
>> Ooh.
>> Yo.
>> That's crazy.
Look at him.
He's beautiful.
>> Oh!
>> Whoa!
>> Oh.
(excited chattering)
(oohing)
>> Damn!
(trumpeting)
(gasping)
>> God.
>> Huge!
>> He's lifting, he's lifting up
stuff so he can throw it.
Look at him. Look at him.
Look at him!
>> Ah!
>> Come on, shh.
>> No.
>> Let's go.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> Good luck and God bless.
>> Good luck, don't get killed.
We need you.
>> Have fun.
>> This frigging elephant in
the jungle, it's here in our
camp, and it's among us all day
because we hear him all day.
But you can't necessarily see
him all the time.
And to actually see one and put
the face to the noise, it's
magnificent.
>> Oh, my God.
The brave boys.
>> Yep.
(leaves rustling)
(branch cracks)
(elephant trumpeting)
>> Oh, he's going that way.
>> Seeing that elephant today
really made me...
step out of the game for a
second.
It just makes you appreciate
the simplicity of life and
the, and the pure things, and...
it makes you appreciate Gabon.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How's it going, Kota?
>> Good.
>> Great.
>> PROBST: Kota, getting your
first look at the new Fang
tribe.
Jacquie voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> They got rid of Jacquie?
>> Oh!
>> Guys, let's focus on the
challenge.
We'll talk about it later.
>> PROBST: A lot of reactions on
Kota.
Surprised?
>> Yeah.
>> Definitely, especially given
her effort yesterday.
So pretty shocking.
>> PROBST: Fang is once again a
new tribe.
Sugar has joined the Fang
tribe, and the numbers are now
even.
All right, you guys ready to
get to today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's challenge, each tribe
will start with a large pile of
fruit.
On my go, you will toss the
fruit to tribe members through
the holes in two walls while
members of the other tribe use
wooden clubs and attempt to
whack that fruit out of the
air.
Once a piece of fruit hits the
ground, you can't pick it up.
The fruit will be weighed at
the end, and the tribe that
manages to collect the most
fruit at the end of five
minutes wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You've been out here
13 days.
Your taste buds are screaming
for something new.
Today's reward will satisfy
that craving.
Your own herb garden.
>> That's awesome.
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: That you can keep
living and keep replenishing.
Also got some salt and oil.
In addition, whatever fruit you
catch, yours to keep.
>> That's pretty good, too.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: All right, give you
a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
On defense, wielding the club
for Fang, we have Crystal at
the front net.
Ace at the back net.
For Kota, Bob is at the front
net.
Charlie is at the back net.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's gotta go through the
holes, and you have to catch it.
Danny catches one right away.
He gets denied by Ace.
>> Go, G!
>> Come on!
Oh, my God, GC!
Throw it high! High!
>> Yo, Matty.
>> PROBST: Matty's caught
something.
Tries to fake out Charlie!
He does! Kenny has it!
Fang first on the board!
Corinne with the left-handed
toss gets denied.
Dan has another.
Gets it rejected right back to
him.
It's a showdown.
>> Out of here!
>> PROBST: Kota's gotta figure
out how to get by Ace if they're
gonna score.
Matty has another for Fang.
Another fake on Charlie, and he
gets it through again, and
Kenny catches it again!
Fang with an early lead.
>> Crystal, do not let anything
through.
>> PROBST: Dan has two pieces of
fruit.
Ace doing a great job with that
club.
>> This is so fun.
>> PROBST: Different story for
Fang.
Matty is working Charlie.
Another big Matty-to-Kenny
connection.
That combination is giving Fang
a big lead right now.
>> Dan, throw two pieces at
once.
>> PROBST: Dan has two pieces of
fruit.
That one connects.
A little banana doesn't weigh
much.
Dan connects with Randy.
>> Atta boy, Dan, perfect.
>> PROBST: Kota starting to get
the hang of it now.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Fang continues to
make connections with those
smaller pieces of fruit.
Dan has half a watermelon and a
pineapple.
Catches the half a watermelon.
That's a lot of weight.
Matty to Kenny continues to
work.
Two minutes left.
Big reception by Randy!
Kota making a good comeback.
>> Got it!
>> PROBST: Huge pineapple caught
by Kenny.
>> Wait for Dan! Wait for Dan!
>> PROBST: Waiting on that left
hand. There it is.
Both baskets look pretty full.
45 seconds left.
We are neck-and-neck.
Dan has a watermelon and a
pineapple.
Annihilates Ace.
The good news is, Ace, nothing
got through.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: We're in the final
seconds of this challenge.
It is very close.
You need to make those last
pieces of fruit count.
Ten seconds left!
Five, four, three,
two, one.
That's it!
Challenge is over!
>> Good job, guys.
>> Like that where you guys had
going two at a time.
That was awesome.
>> PROBST: Good effort.
Very close.
We'll start with Fang.
We're gonna weigh to see who
has the most weight.
16 pounds for Fang.
>> Not bad.
>> PROBST: Kota, you gotta have
16 pounds and an ounce.
You're at ten.
Kota just under 15 pounds.
>> Come on! Come on.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: This is what you have
left.
By two pounds, Kota wins reward.
(all cheering)
All right, Kota, now you have
another big decision to make.
Which member of Fang are you
sending to Exile Island?
>> She might as well have the
mail forwarded there 'cause
Sugar's going again.
(Sugar laughs)
>> That's all right.
I've already named it the
"Sugar Shack."
>> PROBST: Dan, why sending
Sugar again?
>> Just strategy. Purely comedy.
>> Wow.
(Sugar laughing)
>> No, no, because we think if
she finds the idol, she'd had to
play it before the merge, and
we'd like it to get back into
circulation.
>> Whatever.
>> PROBST: I know you don't need
the map.
You could probably show me
where it is better.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: Sugar will return in
time for the next immunity
challenge.
Fang, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Kota, congratulations.
Come get your reward.
>> Thank you.
>> Yes, thank you.
♪ ♪
>> Wow, guys, the plants are
okay.
They're getting water for that.
>> We just got back from our
reward challenge with all of
our new fruits and vegetables,
and so spirits are high around
here, but I feel bad for those
Fang members because I know all
they're eating is rice with no
flavor, and we have tons and
tons of food here.
>> Life is good.
>> The rich are definitely
getting richer here at Kota.
>> All right, so, instead of
the Axis of Evil, we now have
the Evil Empire, guys.
And I think we need to keep our
numbers and stick together once
the merge comes.
I'm gonna need all seven of
you guys.
We're gonna have-- our first
couple of votes after the merge
are gonna have to be unanimous.
I'm an outspoken person and,
and I tend to want to, um, get
people's adrenaline going.
It's a game where you light
a fire under people going up
against, you know, someone you
can coin the "Evil Empire"
absolutely gives us more
motivation to go in there and
win, and not just win by a
little, win by a lot.
And once we get one or two out,
they're gonna crumble, and our
seven will go further.
>> The next immunity challenge
is the most important of the
game.
I think everyone's on the same
page about that.
I think the biggest issue with
Dan is he is so eager to
express his undying, complete,
and total devotion to the new
Kota tribe that no one believes
him.
>> Us seven, as long as we win
the immunity challenges, and us
seven stick together, we're
always gonna have the
numbers on them.
>> On the flip side, Susie's
the opposite of Dan.
She's so quiet that it makes
you think that she's not quite
as on board about stuff that
we've been talking about.
We're now focused on the next 48
hours, which...
>> Crucial.
>> ...is the most important part
of this game right now.
I don't have the confidence
that we get to the merge and
these people have got my back.
>> Come and get your chunk.
Wait, wait, where's Randy?
>> Randy, get up here!
>> All right.
>> The challenge today was fun.
Once again, Kota won, and did I
kick ass or what?
My plan right now is just
continue to win challenges and
not rock the boat, and I will
be Kota yellow to the end.
>> When Kota sent me to
Exile, they said it was for
pure comedy sake, which is
hilarious 'cause I was
thinking the joke's on you.
Better than last time.
Everybody else in the game is
tired and starving and stinky
and dirty as all get-out, and I
am living high on the hog in
Eden all by myself with my own
lake and fruit and comfort, and
I'm a very happy camper now.
I have the idol, and I'd have
to be really dumb to get sent
home next.
But I definitely am happy and
fat. (laughs)
(sighs)
>> Is that all the rice, that
little bag right there?
>> Yeah.
There's about 13 grains of rice.
We can all have two grains.
>> Eat your rice.
>> Don't tell me to do nothing.
>> Okay, Crystal.
Don't tell me what I should be
doing out here.
>> Eat your rice.
>> Shut your mouth!
I'll tell you that much.
I've been out here just a
couple of weeks, and it's way
more difficult than I ever
would have expected.
Not only do you gotta win these
challenges to-to live well out
here, you know, you gotta
deal with these people day in
and day out, 24/7.
>> She is so annoying.
>> It definitely plays tricks
with your head, you know what I
mean?
And it's overwhelming at
times.
It's hard, and I do question,
you know, what am I doing?
>> Is GC sad or something?
>> I don't know. I think so.
>> Like he misses home or...?
>> I don't know.
>> They're cracking at the
edges.
The seams are going.
This argument comes out of
nowhere.
I mean, it was brilliant.
I couldn't have planned it
better.
I'm, like, "These people are
just gonna implode."
I was just sitting back and
enjoying it, you know?
I was, like, "Oh, good, finally,
something's gonna happen."
>> You know, I've kind of had
enough with these people here.
I need to just get back to real
life because this game is-- I
feel like it's-- it's changing
me, and it's not for the better.
♪ ♪
>> We got some mail.
>> Doesn't look so fun.
>> "The gravity of the situation
is you really need to score.
At least prevent the other
tribe, or tonight you will lose
one more."
>> I think we're inside of this.
And it rolls down the hill.
>> Okay, well, whatever it is.
>> Today in the challenge, I
think our chances are slim.
This tribe's floating.
This tribe is all over the
place.
People are starting to become
affected big-time by the, uh,
the elements out here.
GC's losing it.
Crystal's bugging out.
It's all over the place.
It's a bunch of insanity.
♪ ♪
>> GC!
(whistling loudly)
>> We were about to go to the
challenge, and we couldn't
find GC.
Like, everybody was looking for
him because we need our team
there, and he was off on his
own, you know?
>> Are you serious?
We have to leave without him?
>> Yeah.
>> GC!
>> What if he got eaten by,
like, a monkey, dude?
>> Hopefully, he comes back
in time.
But he doesn't like being told
what to do.
You know, that's just how he...
how he rolls.
>> I think we're gonna have to
leave without him.
>> Dude, this is gonna suck.
Want to all scream at the
same time?
>> Okay, ready?
One, two, three.
>> GC!
>> I'm, like, damn, they're
using energy to yell right now.
>> I agree.
I-I'm not giving you any form
of argument.
>> I'm personally getting fed up
with GC.
He just throws these tantrums,
and it is just upsetting to me,
and I'm... I'm just getting fed
up with the tantrums from a
grown adult.
>> GC!
>> I'm not going to the dock
yelling after a grown man.
>> GC?
Did he not hear me?
>> Why? We need you.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Sugar,
returning from Exile Island.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes. Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Dan, I will take back immunity.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, one
member from each tribe will
throw a ball down a cliff
through a series of obstacles
while a blindfolded member of
the other tribe will use a
shield and attempt to block that
ball with the aid of a caller.
Your goal: get your ball past
the defender and into a goal,
scoring points for your tribe.
The goals represent different
point values, five being the
highest.
The tribe with the most points
at the end of five rounds is
safe from Tribal Council.
Losers, you know what that
means.
Fifth person will be voted out
of this game, and they will come
from your tribe.
We'll get started.
♪ ♪
All right, here we go.
The defender for Fang is Ace.
The caller is Sugar.
The defender for Kota is Dan.
The caller is Randy.
First two throwers come up.
Charlie and Matty, grab your
ball and head up.
Your goal is to launch this ball
past the defender.
Defender's job: stop it from
going in the goal.
Dan and Randy, you are stopping
the red ball.
Ace and Sugar, stopping the
yellow ball.
Go!
>> Dan, 15 yards right!
Dan, right, right, right!
(indistinct shouts)
>> PROBST: Kota scores two!
>> Let it go! Let it go!
>> Five, five, five, five, five!
>> PROBST: Fang scores five!
>> Good job, man!
>> Perfect!
>> PROBST: Bit of a learning
curve down there.
Don't get discouraged.
>> Are you gonna come lead me
back?
Or am I just gonna stand here?
>> (laughs): Sorry.
>> PROBST: Fang takes a big
lead: 5-2.
Next two throwers, head up.
Susie throwing for Kota,
GC for Fang.
Go!
>> Right! Right!
>> Right! Right! Right!
>> Forward a little!
Forward a little!
>> PROBST: It blows right past
Ace.
Dan stops his.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Kota scores two more
points!
>> Yes!
>> You did that perfectly.
Just perfectly.
>> PROBST: Ace embarrassed.
>> I can't see anything.
You have to talk.
>> I know.
>> What's happening?
>> Nothing's happening right
now.
>> No, not right this second.
I can hear that.
What's happening with the
course?
>> PROBST: With that, Kota
closes the gap.
They're now down by one: 5-4.
Next two throwers.
>> Come on, Kelly!
>> PROBST: It's Marcus
throwing for Kota,
Kelly throwing for Fang.
Go!
>> Dan, two on your right!
Dan, two on your right!
>> Right, right, right, right!
>> Left, Dan! Dan!
Left right there!
>> Left! Left! Right!
>> PROBST: The balls crossed
each other, and Dan stops his
own ball.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Fang scores two more
points.
>> All right, Kel!
All right, Kel!
>> PROBST: Dan stopped his own
tribe's ball.
>> Hey, we're doing good, Ace!
Good job, buddy!
>> PROBST: Poor communication
for Kota.
>> Just tell me to get out of
the way.
>> PROBST: That mistake cost
Kota.
Fang now jumps ahead: 7-4.
Next two throwers.
It's Corinne for Kota,
Crystal for Fang.
Go!
(grunts)
>> To your right! To your right!
>> Okay, right in the middle.
Stop, stop, stop.
>> Okay, right there, Dan!
>> Right, right, right, right!
>> PROBST: Kota slips right past
Ace!
>> Are you okay?
>> PROBST: Dan catches Fang, as
Kota's gonna fall in...
it does!
Kota scores two!
Fang's lead now back down to a
single point.
What happened?
>> Shield in the face.
>> PROBST: Ace took a shield
into the face.
All right, here we go.
Next two throwers.
>> PROBST: Here's where we
stand: this is the fifth and
final round.
Fang has seven; Kota has six.
One throw left.
It's Bob for Kota,
Kenny for Fang.
This challenge is coming down
to a single throw.
>> I'm on it.
>> PROBST: Go!
(grunts)
>> 20 right! 20 right! 20...
>> Right, right, right!
>> Right there! Right there!
Yes, you got it! You got it!
>> PROBST: Dan stops Fang!
>> Freeze, Ace, freeze, Ace,
freeze!
>> Right there, right there,
right there!
>> PROBST: Oh, Randy pulls a
fast one on Ace!
And that'll do it!
(cheering)
Kota scores!
Kota wins immunity!
(whooping)
>> Nice work!
>> Great job.
>> Great job, Randy.
Where are you?
>> I'm here, man.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: Kota, once again,
immunity is yours.
And, Fang, once again, a date
with me at Tribal Council.
This will be the fifth Tribal
Council.
You've been my guests at four of
them.
All right, guys, grab your
stuff.
Head back to camp.
♪ ♪
>> Good job, you guys.
>> Yeah.
>> We lost another immunity
challenge today.
It's gonna be our fourth time
visiting Tribal Council
tonight, and, um, nobody's
looking forward to it.
>> (laughs) We're the unlucky...
>> This camp is cursed.
>> Bad news.
>> I've noticed.
>> I want to get back on my
grind and focus on, you know,
what's gonna make me happy, man.
Seriously, man.
>> It's all good.
Just trust me.
>> You ask to leave this game,
man, and it's, people pounce on
that.
>> That's bull.
I don't want to hear that.
I don't want to hear it.
Does he think we're going to
be like, "Oh, please stay.
Please stay"?
If you wanna (no audio) go, go.
>> I know.
>> I'm not kissing ass for,
"Oh, please stay."
>> What do we do now?
>> If that's what he wants,
that's what he wants.
I'm voting for GC, hands down.
When we elected him leader, he
quit at that.
He's quit at the challenges and
now he wants to quit the game.
To me, he's a loser.
I have no respect for people
like that that's just gonna
quit.
Being out here that long,
starving, is a mind game
in itself.
So, that's where I stand.
>> Whatever.
He's going home tonight.
>> Good.
>> We're voting out GC.
>> I trust you.
You're paying attention.
>> Well, you know, we're gonna
be (indistinct) to merge
in a tribe that we were dead.
Letting them destroy themselves
is very pleasurable to watch.
Not this time, but at a certain
point, I might call upon you
to use the idol.
>> You haven't told anybody,
have you?
>> No, nobody knows.
>> Okay, good, sweet.
>> Have you hid the idol?
>> Yeah, it's in my bag, but
nobody thinks I have it.
Nobody's going in there.
>> I'm looking. I'm looking.
>> Let me see.
It can't be that small.
>> You're not looking!
Keep a lookout.
Otherwise we'll get in trouble.
>> I knew she had it.
I knew she had it the first...
>> That's why she's so
confident.
>> Right.
>> Tonight is the only night to
blindside her.
That's the freaking... she is
the most dangerous person right
now in this game.
>> So, now we all know that
Sugar has the hidden immunity
idol, and it really changes
things because nobody really
wants to keep GC here longer,
but right now everybody's
scared of that idol.
>> Dude, I don't have time for
quitters but the idol, that's
like, more intense.
(tribal singing)
>> PROBST: Let's talk about the
wear and tear so far.
Ace, are you starting to notice
the impact of being out here
for 15 days now?
>> Uh, a little bit.
I can see it when, you know,
people are running out of belt
loops and, you know, things
that were tight before are
suddenly falling off.
So, yeah, you can notice it,
really.
>> PROBST: GC, the belt loop's
got to be referring to you.
>> Yeah, it's definitely hard,
um, not eating, you know, the
the type of foods that you're
used to eating.
It definitely takes a toll on
you physically and mentally.
But more than the material
things, you start to think
what's more important to you.
Is it staying out here and
starving and dealing with
personalities and losing
challenges, and it's
definitely hard when you just
think about, you know, how much
you could just love to be with
your family and your friends,
you know, and, and how often
you take it for granted.
>> PROBST: Sugar, have you heard
GC talking about home?
>> I've only spent this
afternoon with everybody,
so, I really, uh, I know that
he's feeling like he wants to go
soon and, uh...
>> PROBST: Like he wants to go
soon?
Like go home?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: So, GC, you've talked
about going home.
>> I, you know, I haven't had
the easiest life, man.
And I've suffered all growing up
and just being out here, it's
like, I'm kind of done
suffering.
You know what I mean?
I realize what's important to
me.
But I definitely feel like,
you know, it's... it's hard.
>> PROBST: And right on cue,
Sugar, you're crying.
>> Well, I think we all feel
this way.
I mean, we all miss home and
everything and we are all being
nasty sometimes.
Like, it's weird turning on
people, and I don't think any
of us like that too much.
So, it's probably hardest on our
psyche than physically.
>> PROBST: Matty, tough to hear
a tribe mate talk about wanting
to go home?
'Cause it's gonna affect all
of you in one way or another
if you're out here long enough.
>> You know what?
There's just...
There's no quitting.
You can't give yourself that
option.
Even though you're hurting
right now, that's the answer.
You cannot give yourself that
option.
>> PROBST: Sugar, let's talk
about your experience out here.
You've spent more time on Exile
than you have at the Kota or
the Fang camp.
How concerned are you that I'm
clearly somebody that might be
going home because I don't even
know anybody?
>> Right.
I kind of feel like it could be
me.
I am the one that knows the
least about these people and
they know the least about me.
So, it could just as easily be
me tonight, so, I brought my
bag.
>> PROBST: Kenny, is it a little
frustrating that Sugar keeps
getting sent to Exile?
There's something extremely
valuable out there.
>> Um, yeah, I'm sure it comes
to everybody's mind that, you
know, maybe she found it, but
nobody knows unless she's told
people.
But it is very frustrating.
>> PROBST: So, what kind of
strategy, Sugar, goes through
your mind, whether you have the
idol or not?
Do I let them know I have the
idol?
Do I convince them I don't
have the idol?
>> Nobody really asked me if I
had the idol, actually.
>> PROBST: Does that strike you
as odd?
>> No, not considering
that you're allowed to go
through people's bags.
So, no, it doesn't surprise me.
>> PROBST: So, you think your
bag has been gone through or you
don't know?
>> I don't know.
>> PROBST: Do you keep your bag
with you?
>> Nope.
I keep it out where anybody can
go through it if they want.
>> PROBST: Crystal, crazy to
leave your bag out or crazy
smart?
>> Crazy to leave your bag out.
>> PROBST: Sugar, do you really
truly not care if people know
you have the idol?
>> Maybe there's a sense of
power in knowing that, you
know, somebody has the idol
and maybe you don't want to
vote against them because they
might use it to vote you out.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Sugar, you're up.
>> I'm only voting for you
because you want to go home
and I'm really sorry because
I think you're a really cool
person.
>> My vote is for Kelly
because I had to vote for
somebody.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: GC.
GC.
Two votes GC.
Kelly.
Two votes GC; one vote Kelly.
GC.
Three votes GC.
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon: GC.
That's four; that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
GC, your tribe has spoken.
You guys have endured
a lot in your first 15 days.
One thing is for certain: you
are going to have to dig deep
if you're going to last in this
game.
Grab your torches and head back
to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I just don't know who would
be my potential Benedict Arnold.
Until merge, on your girl,
you're not gonna stab me
in the back.
>> I made a pact with Ace.
>> Deal.
>> This is going to be the
start of a great run for me.
I have complete supremacy.
>> For all the people who, who
might say that I quit or I
just gave up, call it what you
want.
The back-stabbing and the
lying, that's the part that I
really didn't agree with.
I never expected it to be this
hard.
The vote for Kelly was the
throwaway vote.
She was the one who I connected
with the least.
I got the utmost respect for
anybody who makes it, who even
tries out, and whoever has
walked in my shoes.