>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
(roaring)
(twittering)
(chattering)
18 Americans embarked on a
journey to one of the most
remote regions of Africa.
Welcome to Survivor: Gabon,
Earth's last Eden.
The diverse group included
a high school physics teacher,
a world championship video game
player, and an Olympic athlete.
>> I am a 2004 gold medalist in
the women's 4 x 400-meter relay.
>> PROBST: As they split into
two tribes, Ace and Sugar
connected right off the bat.
>> I don't think it would be
appropriate for a photographer
not to have a model.
Sugar, please.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: The tribes were
called Fang, in red, and, Kota,
wearing yellow.
Go!
They immediately raced for
individual immunity and extra
food.
Marcus has the idol for Kota.
For Fang, GC grabs the idol.
Fang lost the challenge
by a landslide.
Kota wins corn and beans!
From the very beginning, Kota
was a tribe that could do no
wrong.
>> Our morale was super-high.
We're all excited.
We love our team.
>> PROBST: The yellow tribe
was in perfect harmony.
>> I felt a little yoga would
really get our energy flowing,
the chakras would be all in
time.
>> PROBST: Almost.
>> Ace is kind of getting on my
nerves.
>> PROBST: Kota's smallest tribe
mate, Paloma, was making waves.
>> Ace is getting on my nerves.
He does not shut up.
>> PROBST: But Kota's problems
seem insignificant compared
to Fang's.
After only six days, the red
tribe was starting to look like
one of the worst tribes in
Survivor history.
>> This tribe is hopeless.
They're idiots.
>> PROBST: They lost an immunity
challenge badly, and voted out
one of their best athletes.
They selected a tribe leader,
GC, and he quit the next day.
>> I didn't want to be a leader.
I'm not going to let y'all force
me to be the leader.
>> PROBST: Gillian's not
helping.
Fang is falling behind.
They lost yet another immunity
challenge, and then finally,
they did something that was
completely out of character.
They made a unified decision.
They unanimously voted out their
oldest and weakest player.
Gillian, the tribe has spoken.
>> Bummer.
>> PROBST: 16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Thank God for another night.
>> Hell, yeah, man.
Whatever happens, we made it
another night, you guys.
>> Tribal Council was
a no-brainer.
Gillian, you got to go.
We got rid of a major physical
weak link.
>> Tomorrow is going to be a
new day.
>> We got to win tomorrow.
We have to.
(clamoring)
>> And I don't care if it's
physical or whatever-- bring
it on.
Ahh! Okay.
(laughter)
>> I would like to start
winning, but the tribe that I
have, I still don't believe
it's possible.
>> Are you trying to break that?
>> The problem is that they're
stupid.
I really shouldn't blame them
for being complete idiots, but
they are.
They don't know it, but,
but they are.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
>> Oh, man, we're getting it
cracking out here.
>> It's day seven, and we're
over halfway finished with our
rice.
Someone had the bright idea
of three meals a day.
You know, this is Survivor.
Three meals a day?
It's ridiculous.
We're running low on rice.
We're running out.
It's not "maybe." It's a fact.
I mean, I love three meals
a day, but can we compromise
at two?
Two meals a day?
>> I can.
>> I'm fine with two.
>> I just, I don't know.
I just think, uh, everybody
was eating so much at first.
I remember throwing away
a half a pot of rice the first
day.
That wasted so much of our rice.
And now I'm suffering because
some people chose to do that
early on.
>> I'm not suffering.
>> I am.
>> In my opinion, the cancer in
the tribe is GC.
He cannot be told anything.
And our tribe is going to
continue to have problems until
that cancer is excised.
>> Randy, are you, like,
the leader of the tribe now?
>> No.
We're just sitting here
talking, dude.
>> I'm not...
>> If you want to start, we'll
start it.
>> It just seems like lately,
like the last couple of days,
you kind of been trying to step
up into the leadership role.
I don't know if that's what you
want to do, but you sure are
jumpy about it.
>> No, we decided this tribe
doesn't need a leader.
So what's your point?
Are you asking me if I want
to be leader?
Okay, the answer's no.
And, you know, I don't want
to talk about it anymore.
Drop it.
>> I don't have to drop nothing,
man.
I can ask you something if I
want.
>> And I can just ignore you
then.
>> You can do that if you want.
>> I don't think we've pulled
together as a team.
We'd have a much better chance
if we were more unified and
thinking of this as a team,
rather than, you know, fighting
amongst each other.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Ooh!
>> Whoo!
>> A fish.
It's amazing.
>> Yay!
>> Our hero.
>> My alliance right now is
with Marcus, Corinne, and
Jacquie.
Beyond that, I think Paloma and
Kelly are really tight.
And Sugar is attached to Ace.
And I definitely think Bob is
woo-able, and can be used as a
swing vote.
So there is always the concern
that the other five might bond
together, but I think the other
five are so all over the place,
that we'll be able to keep the
four together.
>> It's his way or no way.
>> Like, right now, they're
just, like, he's like the king,
and everybody's, like, bowing
down to him.
I just want to gag every time
he opens his mouth.
>> I know.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> For some reason, me and Ace
decided we had some kind of
connection.
I trust Ace.
And I believe that he's going
to take care of me as much as
he can.
>> You guys!
>> Tree mail!
>> Okay, ready?
"This head-to-head battle
requires a well-balanced team.
To win some camp comfort,
you'll kick and you'll scream."
Totally bedding.
>> Bedding!
>> We've got water.
>> Right.
>> I mean, obviously, I'm not
going to say let's throw
the challenge, but I'm
saying I'd rather we put out
people that are stronger today,
so we have those people that
are stronger for the immunity
challenge.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> Because I can live without
bedding, but I'd rather not go
to Tribal.
>> Everybody seems to adore Ace
at this point because right now
everybody's just bowing down to
him.
They think he's the king, but I
can see through it, so I'm not
blinded by it.
But you know, just from talking
to Kelly, I know she has the
same frustration.
We both are over him.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
♪ ♪
Kota getting your first look
at the new Fang Tribe.
Gillian voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
You guys ready to get to
today's reward challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, one member of each
tribe will be stationed at a
post.
On my go, two members of the
other tribe will race out and
attempt to remove you from that
post and drag you through the
sand to the finish.
First tribe to get the member
of the other tribe across the
finish line scores a point.
One note: players can swap
positions each round.
First tribe to score two points
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Comfort.
>> Yeah!
(applause)
>> PROBST: Blankets, hammock,
pillows, mat.
In addition, the winning tribe
will send one member from the
losing tribe to Exile Island.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> You know it.
>> PROBST: Because this
challenge requires a specific
number of men and women, Fang,
you will sit out one man.
Kota, you must sit out three
women.
Fang, who's going to sit out
for you?
>> I am.
>> Kenny.
>> PROBST: Ken's going to be
the man sitting out for Fang.
Kota, who's it going to be?
>> Us three.
>> PROBST: Corinne, Jacquie,
Kelly.
Everybody else, head up
to the start.
Dan is first on the post for
Fang.
Ace, first on the post for Kota.
He's yawning.
Wow, you're that relaxed.
The attackers for Kota are
Charlie and Marcus.
The attackers for Fang:
GC and Matty.
Here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's going to be good and
physical.
Dan, hanging on tight.
The big battle between Matty
and Ace and GC.
>> Come on, y'all!
Let's go!
>> PROBST: Marcus and Charlie
got Dan off the post.
Ace proving very strong for
Kota.
Marcus and Charlie slowly
inching Dan toward that finish
line.
>> Come on, Matty!
>> PROBST: Ace not budging
against GC and Matty.
Marcus and Charlie inching him
closer, little by little.
(cheering)
GC, you got to dig deeper
than that.
>> Come on, GC!
>> Come on, Charlie!
>> PROBST: Kota very close.
GC has given up.
Kota scores the first point!
Kota leads 1-zip.
>> PROBST: Kota leads 1-zip.
Next round, Susie will be on
the post for Fang.
Paloma will be on the post for
Kota.
The attackers for Kota:
Bob and Sugar.
The attackers for Fang:
Randy and Crystal.
If Kota scores this point,
Kota wins reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
This match looks a little more
uneven with Crystal and Randy
on the very small Paloma.
This could be over quickly.
>> You're done!
You're done.
>> PROBST: Randy and Crystal
have Paloma off the post very
fast.
They're dragging her up the
hill.
>> There you go.
You're done.
>> PROBST: Fang scores!
We're tied, 1-1.
>> Yeah!
Get some!
Come on and get some!
I'm trying to sleep good
tonight.
>> PROBST: All right, we are
tied 1-1.
We're back to the original
match-up: Ace and Dan on the
poles.
The attackers are different
this time.
Marcus and Bob attacking for
Kota.
And Crystal and Matty are the
attackers for Fang.
This is a final round.
Playing for reward.
Kota would like to make sure
Fang does not taste victory.
Fang is desperate for a victory.
Survivors ready?
Go!
This is it right here.
>> Come on, Crystal!
>> PROBST: You need to dig deep
like you've never dug before.
Dan holding on tight against
Marcus and Bob.
Ace not budging against Matty
and Crystal.
Which tribe wants it more?
>> Crystal, we need this win!
>> PROBST: Matty has the top
half of Ace off of the post.
Crystal, working on the legs.
Bob and Marcus have Dan off the
post.
Dan hanging on with his last
arm.
>> Nice, Crystal!
>> PROBST: Crystal and Matty
have Ace off the post, and they
are dragging him!
Marcus and Bob starting to make
some progress.
We are neck and neck.
Ace trying to get away.
A big takedown!
This is a war.
Bob and Marcus fighting hard on
Dan.
Crystal's starting to drag
Ace again.
Fang getting closer to their
first victory!
Dan fighting them off.
>> Don't give up!
>> PROBST: Ace knocks Crystal
down.
>> Crystal!
Do it!
>> I can't hold on much longer!
>> PROBST: Dan screaming for
some help.
Matty now pulling Ace.
Who's got more will?
You got to cross the plane.
You got to get him across.
Fang wins reward!
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
>> Yes!
>> Good job!
>> One, two, three-- Fang!
>> PROBST: Fang,
congratulations.
Crystal, you look very
emotional.
>> We had to go out here and
fight like warriors in order to
get some blankets and some
comfort, but it was worth it.
>> PROBST: Fang, big decision to
make.
Who are you going to send from
Kota to go to Exile Island?
>> We're going to go with
someone sweet.
So we're going to pick Sugar.
>> I knew that.
>> PROBST: How'd you know that?
I knew that they were going
to pick me 'cause they think
I'm dumb, but they haven't
talked to me yet.
>> PROBST: Well, the bad news
for you, Sugar, you're going
to be away from camp, and as you
know, that's never a good thing.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: The good news is,
waiting for you on Exile, a clue
to the location of a hidden
immunity idol.
Got your stuff?
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: Map to Exile.
Kota, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
All right, Fang, nice job.
Get your reward.
Head on out.
>> Hammock.
(cheering)
>> Nice.
Everybody, nice.
>> Good job, man.
That challenge felt so good.
It felt good for the other
tribe to feel the pain that we
have been feeling to walk away
with your heads down.
>> How fun is winning?
How awesome is it to come back
winning?
>> You held on.
>> The reason I held on so long
'cause I got my energy from
Matty and from you.
Coming back into camp, we were
feeling like a team.
Finally feeling like we're
going to start creating a little
bit of a roll here.
I was losing it and you heard
me yelling.
>> I'm all, "Come on, bitch!
Come on, bitch!"
(laughter)
>> No, you guys did awesome.
>> I mean, we had-- we moved
our forces back in perfect
retreat, which was the point.
>> Exactly.
>> But we did take out our
strongest girls, you know?
I mean, it was a great, great
decision.
>> That was such a brilliant
strategy.
>> It's hard when, like...
I mean, their three strongest,
and one of the them was the
girl, it's like...
>> Yeah.
>> No.
Nobody would of.
>> Crystal, which is on their
team, is huge.
Especially compared to me.
Like, I'm the shortest person
alive, so compared to Crystal,
like, I mean, I just had no
chance.
It was kind of weird that,
like, Ace decided to put me on
the pole instead of Sugar, but,
like with Ace, it's kind of
like it's his way or the
highway.
>> We should have put Kelly in
instead of Paloma.
I'm not sure why we sat the
three of you guys out.
>> It would have been fine to
put her in for a puzzle or
something, but...
>> Yeah, but what if it wasn't
a puzzle?
>> Yeah, that's...
>> That's fine.
>> We're short two pillows.
>> Big deal.
>> We'll be fine.
>> It's not fine when it's,
like, we still have to catch
fish for her and catch fish for
her tonight, and keep the traps
and do all the other stuff.
It's, like, I don't know, we're
just stuck with Paloma.
>> Yeah.
>> It was a bit hard, you know,
watching Paloma just give up.
Yeah, I think her lack of, um...
motivation, let's say, just sort
of sealed what we were all
thinking already.
Sort of crossed and dotted the
"T"s on her contract of death.
So whatever.
>> "In this garden of Eden,
a difficult choice you'll face.
One choice provides an apple.
One choice provides direction.
Spend your time in idle comfort
or seek idol protection."
Going for the clue.
Getting in that cage and having
comfort, it would have been
nice.
But it would have been really
stupid because I'm pretty sure
since I'm only the second person
sent to Exile Island, that the
idol is still out there.
"Across the lake you see so
well, there lies a sandy crater.
The object hidden in its floor
will surely help you later."
Looks like I got to go through
a jungle.
No problem.
(gasps): Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
(screams)
This is not my normal thing,
obviously.
I'm not a camper.
I don't like to be dirty.
I think I've gone too far.
This time, I've gone too far.
Yeah... I'm lost.
I did Survivor 'cause I thought
it might help me grow up
a little bit and get a thicker
skin, and get over...
not get over, but deal with...
my father's death-- I can't
even say it.
My father passed away seven
months ago.
I'm trying to, trying to keep
it together because when I stay
in survival mode, then I don't
get like this.
I'm sure I'll be a stronger
person by the end of it all.
Playing this game will help me
at this time in my life.
Oh, thank God!
(laughs)
Holy...
Oh, my God.
Did I find... the thing?
Or is this a joke?
"Now turn around, go back
towards the lake.
On one tree hill climb for
salvation's sake."
What?
That looks like it could be one
tree.
Maybe I'll...
start with this one.
Oh... cool.
I don't really know how to play
this game, but I'm learning
really quick.
My confidence is built up a
little bit more with each new
thing I do.
I'm a lot tougher than I
thought I was.
"Walk along a yonder creek.
Beneath the burned wood is the
thing you seek."
Oh, Lord...
Okay, cool.
Hey, uh... can you help me out
with this?
"Through creatures unknown
you'll have to wade among
the limbs that reach skyward
your deliverance shall be made."
Hopefully the idol, right?
Not another clue.
Oh, Lordy, Lordy, Lordy.
I'm going to have to
♪ Wade in the water. ♪
That's a big, old tree in the
middle of the water.
Maybe that's it.
Oh, Lordy.
I'm going over to that tree.
'Cause it looks like it might
have some good hiding spots.
Oh, my God.
Don't be scared.
(screaming)
(groans)
That was so scary.
(gasps): Oh, my God!
I found it!
Okay, good.
Thank God.
When Fang sent me to Exile, I
thought maybe they thought I
was dumb, and that I'd never
find the idol, no way.
I can't believe I found it and
the lawyer didn't.
How funny is that?
That's funny.
But my dad's been with me this
whole time, so I feel like he's
been helping me.
Um, he's here.
Thank you, my friend.
You were awesome.
(laughs)
Thank you very much.
♪ ♪
>> Uh-huh.
>> And those are the two that
I'm flip-flopping with.
And I know you like Sugar.
>> I like Sugar as a person.
You know, she's loyal.
And loyalty stands a lot for
this game.
You know that.
>> Yeah.
>> I think we can trust Sugar
longer than we can Paloma.
>> Ace is putting himself at
at risk by doing this
manipulation.
By calling out Paloma, he's
protecting Sugar big-time.
He wants to keep Sugar.
I can see why.
If she makes it to the jury,
she will vote for him, but that
can irritate people and it
worries people.
And that's what worries me.
>> It'll definitely be Paloma
and then Sugar.
>> Yeah.
>> Or Sugar, then Paloma.
I mean, they're going.
Ace is doing something very
stupid.
He's bringing Sugar to the end
because she's weak.
She needs him.
I'll tell you this much.
I have, you know, Jacquie,
Marcus, Charlie.
You know, we're all in your
book.
As long as, you know, you feel
the same way we do, we're all
in it together.
>> Yeah.
>> And there's five of us.
So it's... we can pick whoever
we want.
We are in the majority.
I think Bob responds really
well to bold, confident moves.
When I was speaking to him,
I had to speak to him like,
"Here's the deal.
These are the four.
You're the fifth.
That's all you need to know.
It's the majority.
We're getting rid of this one."
That's it.
And it doesn't really matter
'cause we're five.
So lock it down.
That's it.
>> Good point.
>> None of us are looking
to take Bob to the end.
However, we need him for
numbers, and I think that we can
trust him.
>> Tree mail.
>> "Slip, slide, splash and run.
The stakes are high, but you'll
have some fun.
Who is bright and who is slow?
Know the difference or be the
next to go."
>> Oh, no!
>> (gasps): Yay!
>> Yay!
I knew our swimsuits were
in there!
>> Yay!
>> I think the next immunity
challenge is the most crucial
one that we've had at this
point.
Their one victory has given
them some hope.
Crushing that hope is going to
send them to another level of
despair.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Sugar,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Sugar.
>> Hey, babe.
>> Oh!
That was really wrong.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: Don't look at me.
I didn't send you.
It's the game.
All right, you guys ready
to get to today's immunity
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
I will take it back again.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, one at a
time, you will launch yourself
down a slippery slide and into
the water.
You'll then swim out to
retrieve a covered number tile
and race back.
Once you've collected all six
tiles, the remaining tribe
member will use those numbered
tiles to solve a math puzzle.
The answer will reveal the
combination to a chest.
First tribe to open their
chest and raise their tribe
flag... wins immunity.
Losers, Tribal Council, where
somebody will be going home.
Kota, you have two extra
members.
Who's going to sit out this one?
Paloma and Sugar.
I'll also give you a minute
to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, Bob and Ken are
waiting to solve puzzle.
Everybody else is going down
the slide.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
It's Crystal and Kelly first
down.
Kelly does it perfectly.
Crystal takes a hard hit.
Both are in the water at the
same time.
Crystal's tall enough she can
actually run to get her first
puzzle piece.
>> Come on, Kelly!
>> PROBST: Kelly coming back.
>> Come on, Crystal!
>> Run!
>> PROBST: Crystal out of the
water first for Fang.
>> Run, Crystal, run!
>> PROBST: Susie on the course.
>> Come on, Kel.
>> PROBST: Fang with a
good-sized lead right off the
bat.
Corinne hits the course.
>> That was awesome!
>> Come on, Susie!
>> PROBST: Susie has the second
piece to this puzzle.
Corinne quickly gets her number.
She's heading back.
Making up a lot of time on
Susie.
>> Come on, Sue, faster!
>> You got it!
You got it!
>> PROBST: Fang has lost all of
their lead now.
Charlie on the course for Kota.
>> Yeah, Charlie!
>> PROBST: Kota now has the
lead.
>> Yeah, Charlie!
>> PROBST: GC on the course
for Fang.
That's how you do it.
Charlie out of the water,
heading back for Kota.
Kota has three tiles back.
Fang, still with two.
Kota still with a good-sized
lead.
Randy on the course for Fang.
>> Come on, Randy!
>> PROBST: Jacquie out of the
water for Kota.
Two numbers left.
Ace flips over twice.
Randy needs to pick it up.
Fang has lost more time.
Dan on the course for Fang.
Still looking to win that first
immunity challenge.
Ace holding on to Kota's lead.
>> Ace!
>> PROBST: Kota has one number
left in the water.
Fang has two more left.
A big launch.
Marcus heading out for that
sixth and final number for Kota.
Dan finally out of the water
for Fang.
Matty's going to have to make
up a lot of time.
Marcus out of the water with
the sixth and final number for
Kota.
It's now up to Bob to solve the
puzzle.
>> Okay, Bob!
You can do it!
>> PROBST: Matty out of the
water with that sixth and final
number.
>> Go, Ken!
>> PROBST: Ken racing now,
trying to catch up.
Got a physics teacher going
head-to-head with a video game
expert.
You don't need to be a math
major to figure this out.
You just need to be able to
concentrate.
Read it carefully.
Rearrange the numbers.
"The sum of both end values will
equal the sum of the middle two.
The last number is equal to the
second, minus the third, and is
one less than the one before
it."
>> Do it! Do it, then!
Try it!
>> PROBST: Bob thinks he might
have it.
Make those numbers into a
combination.
If you're right, the chest will
open.
No, he doesn't have it.
>> I think I got it.
>> PROBST: Ken thinks he has it.
Ken tries it.
He's not right.
Try to look at this puzzle
again.
Maybe you're putting a comma
where it doesn't belong or
reading a word wrong.
>> Oh, are these the end values?
>> PROBST: Bob thinks he might
have figured it out suddenly.
>> I think I got it, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Ken thinks he has it
again.
>> I do, too.
>> PROBST: Bob thinks he has it.
Both tribes trying it.
Either one of these guys are
right, immunity for their tribe.
>> Pull the damn handle, Bob!
>> PROBST: Bob tries it.
He's wrong, once again.
Ken has it right for Fang.
Fang wins immunity!
(cheers)
>> We did it!
>> Oh, my God!
>> That's simple math.
>> Fang!
>> PROBST: Fang,
congratulations.
Back-to-back wins.
This time for immunity.
This game is changing.
(applause)
Kota, date with me tonight at
Tribal Council where the third
person will be voted out of
this game.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Fang, you guys going to miss me
at Tribal Council?
>> You need to get to know them
a little bit better.
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> But the clues are not
freaking easy.
I had to find my way through,
like, a big desert.
Saw a spot with this map
and I kind of read it wrong
or something.
I think I played off the fact
that I won the idol pretty
well.
I don't think anybody has
a clue that I got it.
I'm not too bad at this.
I'm a lot better than I
thought, for sure.
>> So I can hang on to this
thing for a while, maybe.
>> Yeah, hang on to it.
I mean, I'd obviously, not
bring it to Tribal tonight,
but I mean, I'd bring it to
Tribal generally.
>> I just had a very nice
conversation in the canoe,
being told that Sugar has the
immunity idol.
And we're going to hopefully
dominate this game.
>> Paloma tonight.
>> Paloma's dead.
>> Yeah, okay.
>> Um, Kelly's pretty dead after
that.
>> Awesome.
I'm pretty excited.
>> Now, we're all prepping for
the coupe de grace, being
Tribal Council, and the
dismissal of little Miss Paloma.
>> Strategically, I'm, like,
the animals out in the wilds.
I just watch.
Just watch, and then I'm going
to pounce on someone and eat
them up.
Has Ace made an alliance with
you yet?
He's made an alliance with
everybody else.
>> He has?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> He's not said one word to me.
He's not said one to me 'cause
he doesn't like me.
I mean, he's trying everything
he can to get rid of me, like
putting me on the pole instead
of Sugar.
Anyway, think about it.
He doesn't want to get rid of
Sugar.
Ace doesn't want to, and Ace
is pretty much running the game.
>> Hmm.
>> It's really crazy.
Just keep your eyes out because
he's really, really sneaky.
Like, I'll just say what I need
to say really fast till I get
people to think and get their
brains going and make them,
like, all crazy and, like,
thinking.
Ace might be, you know, strong
as an ox and I might be as weak
as a mouse, but we're both
50/50.
People want him out because
he's strong.
People might want me out because
we're weak.
>> He's not running the show,
Paloma.
>> Well, I mean, not...
I mean, personally, I don't
really care.
I can't stand the guy.
>> Well, let me see what I can
think up.
That's not happening.
I really can't stand Ace.
I'm not sure that that accent is
real.
I think he's a con artist.
I would like it see him go home
sooner rather than later.
I am afraid if Ace goes with us
to the merge he will be the
first one to flip because he's
on the outskirts of our
alliance.
So I went on a walk with
Paloma.
>> Yeah?
She tried me to be in an
alliance with her.
And she was like, "Ace is really
dangerous."
She goes "The only reason why
Ace made a point to force me to
go on the post is so that
everyone could see how bad I
was."
She's like, "Everyone knew
who's..."
>> I think that could be partly
true.
>> It's 100% true.
Afterwards...
I know this because afterwards
Ace was like, "Did you see how
good a job..."
>> Sugar wants him.
>> What, are you...
>> And she can do it for two
seconds, like this.
>> Not even.
It's a problem.
Ace needs to get out of here
before the merge because we
can't have that.
>> You're smart at this game.
There definitely is a short-term
benefit to getting rid of our
weakest players because then we
can trounce, you know, the other
team and not have to vote off
other people.
But Ace is the biggest concern
because Ace has been playing
Sugar like a pawn.
>> "I'm taking her to the end
because she's easy.
She follows what I say, like..."
>> They're going to pull out
all the stops at the end.
>> Getting rid of Paloma,
whatever, that can be done
later.
You want to get rid of Ace
earlier before he gains
momentum before we merge.
That's more important.
I don't know. It's hard to say.
I dislike so many people on
this damn tribe that it's like,
it's a toss-up.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
is a torch.
Grab a torch, approach a flame,
dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire, you
are still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
So, finally, we get a chance to
talk.
So, Corinne, first Tribal
Council, what do you base the
vote on?
>> Everybody has their own
opinion of who should be voted
out, but the idea is that you
want one opinion together, so
that you have as little
dissension among the group as
possible.
>> PROBST: Ace, that seems
incredibly pie-in-the-sky.
"Let's come to one group
consensus on who we're going to
vote out?"
>> I think this early in the
game, the most important thing
is what strengthens the tribe
and makes us stronger for
challenges.
>> PROBST: Sugar, let's talk
about Exile Island.
That's a long time to be alone
this early in the game.
What do you draw on?
>> Well, um...
I thought about my dad.
Damn it.
Just because I lost my dad
recently, and...
And....
>> PROBST: It's got to be tough.
>> I missed everyone.
>> Marcus, there are two ways
to play in regards to the idol.
One is "Don't try to flush it
out 'cause I don't have it."
The other is, "I got it."
>> You're absolutely right.
I mean, I think Sugar's
choosing, if she does have it,
to let her outside reflect
something completely different
than the insides, and, you
know, if that's the case, more
power to her.
It's probably the way I would
play it myself.
>> PROBST: When you got with
this group, who jumped out at
you you as, wow, interesting.
>> Um, I think our tribe
actually has a lot of those
people, but, I mean, Ace was a
really interesting guy from the
start, and he and I seem to work
well together and have a lot of
similar ideas.
>> PROBST: Paloma, did Ace stand
out to you as having a big
personality?
>> Yeah, definitely.
Ace is, like, the head honcho at
our campsite.
>> PROBST: How do you feel about
that, him being the big guy?
>> I mean, like, he can be the
big guy all he wants.
I really could care less.
But, I mean, as far as I'm
concerned, I'm not even going to
go there.
>> PROBST: You're not even going
to go where?
>> Like, do the whole, like,
"Ace is my hero" type thing,
like...
>> PROBST: So, Ace is clearly
not your hero.
>> No, not at all.
>> PROBST: Ace, does that
surprise you to hear that?
>> Not particularly.
I think we have the capacity to
rub each other the wrong way.
>> PROBST: Kelly, do you think
Ace is an asset to your tribe?
>> Um, in some cases, because
he's almost condescending in a
way.
>> PROBST: How is condescending
a good thing?
>> It's not a good thing at all
sometimes.
Um, say, we're cooking rice or
something, he'll be like, "Oh,
I thought we were going to make
water."
Like, if somebody wants to make
rice, let us make rice.
We don't necessarily need water
right now.
>> PROBST: Ace, concerned at all
that you have two people that
are coming up saying, "By the
way, I got two votes and..."
>> Of course, you know.
You can never walk into Tribal
Council without being scared.
>> He doesn't have his bag with
him, so he can't be that
worried.
>> There's nothing I really
wanted to take from camp.
>> Think you guys would have
been maybe brother-sister in
another life?
>> Maybe, in another world,
1,000 years from now, when I'm
dead.
>> PROBST: Wow.
All right, Marcus, you have an
immunity idol around your neck.
It is only good at tonight's
Tribal Council.
You can, obviously, assign it
to somebody if you want or make
sure are you safe and keep it.
>> I think I'm going to hang on
to it this time.
>> PROBST: All right.
Tonight, Marcus is safe.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Kelly, you're up.
>> This is pretty much
self-explanatory.
>> Unfortunately, you know
exactly why you're leaving.
It's for the strength of the
tribe.
Best of luck.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Paloma.
Ace.
One vote Paloma; one vote Ace.
Two votes Ace; one vote Paloma.
Paloma.
We're tied: two votes Paloma;
two votes Ace.
Paloma.
Three votes Paloma;
two votes Ace.
Paloma.
That's four votes Paloma;
two votes Ace.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon: Paloma.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Paloma, the tribe has spoken.
Well, the truth is, you've lost
back-to-back challenges,
and now your first tribe member.
Fang clearly has the momentum.
Question is, can you get it
back?
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Crystal, Kenny, and GC
are not with me.
>> PROBST: A tribe divided...
>> The tightest three is right
here.
>> PROBST: Divides again.
Today, you're going on to rank
your tribe from top to bottom.
And the game is turned upside
down.
>> This is not looking too good
for a pimp.
>> So, I got voted off.
Um, first person on my tribe to
go.
These past nine days in Gabon
have been amazing.
Definitely been an experience,
something I've never ever done
before.
Good luck to the whole Kota
tribe.
I hope you guys do awesome.
But definitely, let's just put
it this way:
If Ace wins a million dollars,
I will probably never watch
Survivor again.