(roaring)
(trumpeting)
(growls)
♪ ♪
(hooting)
>> JEFF PROBST: This is Gabon,
one of the last untouched places
on the planet.
♪ ♪
18 Americans have been flown
across the world and dropped
here in the wild with nothing
but their street clothes.
They're being led to one of the
most remote places in Africa.
They come from different walks
of life.
>> I am a 2004 Olympic gold
medalist in the women's 4 x 400-
meter relay.
I'm gonna use my blazing speed
to win the hell out of this
game.
>> In the wintertime, I teach
high school physics,
In the summertime, I lobster,
do commercial fishing.
>> I wasn't the best kid.
As a teenager and stuff, I was
doing some things I'm not proud
of, but you know, I'm grown now,
and I can't believe that I
actually have a chance to win a
million dollars.
>> I'm from America, but I grew
up, very well, going to
different countries, flying on
Concorde and being in the best
hotels, Swiss money.
>> PROBST: Forced to work
together, they must create a new
society while battling the
elements and each other.
>> This is Earth's last Eden
and I can see why.
It's untouched land, and it's
amazing.
>> PROBST: They must learn to
adapt or they'll be voted out.
In the end, only one will
remain to claim the
million-dollar prize.
>> It's completely awesome to
be thrown into the world that
is about to start.
It was just like, okay, here we
go.
>> PROBST: 39 days, 18 people,
one survivor.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
(trumpeting)
PROBST: Welcome to Survivor:
Gabon: Earth's Last Eden.
You guys ready to get started?
>> Absolutely.
>> You know it.
>> PROBST: First thing I want
you to do is introduce yourself
and say what you do.
>> What's up, everybody?
My name is Danny.
I'm a maintenance supervisor.
>> I'm Runaround Bob.
I'm a physics teacher.
>> My name is Jacquie, and I do
medical device sales.
>> My name is Ken.
I'm a professional video-game
player and a college student.
I'm number one in the world at
video games.
I'm a huge time strategist, but
I am very shy, and in the game
of Survivor, I am the underdog.
>> Hey, everybody, I'm Marcus.
I'm in the medical field.
Good to see you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Good to see you.
>> Hi, I'm Charlie.
I'm a management consultant.
>> Matty. I'm a personal
trainer.
>> Hi, Jeff.
I'm Jesusita Smith.
Everybody calls me "Susie."
I am a part-time hairdresser
and I'm a mom and a wife.
>> Hi, my name is Paloma.
I'm a student and I'm a server.
>> My name's Randy, and I am a
videographer.
I edit wedding videos for
a living, but I'm not the
most positive person in the
world.
I'm not a big fan of marriage.
I will never get married myself.
I'm almost sure of it.
>> Hello, Jeff.
My name's Ace, and I'm a
photographer.
>> Hi, everyone, my name is
Crystal, and I'm a preschool
teacher and a full-time mom.
Even though I am an Olympic
gold medalist in track and
field, I have no intention on
telling anyone what my real
occupation is.
>> My name's Kelly.
I'm an assistant manager and
buyer for one of the high-end
retail stores in Chicago.
>> Hi, everybody.
I'm Corinne and I do
pharmaceutical sales.
I'm going to be a total bitch
and I'm gonna get rid of who I
have to get rid of and I'm gonna
hurt people's feelings and I'm
gonna laugh when people cry and
I'm gonna own it.
>> I'm Dan, and for five years I
was an attorney, and I'm
currently finding myself.
>> PROBST: You're gonna have 39
days to find yourself out here,
if you're lucky.
Woman in the purple.
>> Michelle. Hi. AKA
"woman in the purple."
Um, I work in film.
I help music supervisors and
editors.
>> I'm Sugar, and I'm a retro
pin-up model.
>> I'm Gillian, and I'm a wife,
a mother, a grandmother of four,
and I'm a nurse.
>> PROBST: Okay, in Gabon it is
tradition that the elders
typically make the big
decisions and are the leaders.
In keeping with that tradition,
I need the two oldest people.
>> Bob?
I'm gray enough to be old.
>> PROBST: Okay.
>> I'm 57.
>> All right, looking good,
Bob, looking good.
>> PROBST: Nobody can beat 57.
All right, Bob, and it's
Gillian?
>> Gillian.
>> PROBST: Take a spot on the
mat, either one.
You guys figure it out.
Red or yellow.
>> You want that?
>> PROBST: You guys all right
with those choices?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, we're
going to choose tribes.
(gasps)
Each time you make a selection,
you can choose a man or a woman.
It doesn't matter.
Obviously, these are big
decisions.
You are forming your tribe, and
you're going off very little
information.
A name and what somebody says
they do, if that is what they
do.
(chuckles)
Rock, paper, scissor to see
who chooses first.
>> Okay, ready, one, two, three?
Got her.
>> PROBST: Paper covers rock.
Bob will choose first.
And how it will work is you will
make the first choice, then you
will choose.
Then the person who was chosen
will make the next choice.
These are individual decisions.
All right, Bob, your first
choice of who you want on your
tribe.
>> I'm bad at names.
Can I take Baldy?
(laughter)
>> PROBST: The guy with shaved
head.
You want to tell him your name?
>> Thanks, Bob. It's Ace.
>> Nice to be able to talk to
you.
>> I'm going to talk to you
today.
>> The woman that was standing
next to Ace.
>> My name is Crystal.
>> Hey, Crystal. Come on over.
>> Ace, it's now your choice.
>> I don't think it would be
appropriate for a photographer
not to have a model.
Sugar, please.
>> Yes.
(contestants chuckle)
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: Sugar joins Ace and
Bob.
Crystal, your choice.
>> Suzanne, come on home.
>> I knew it.
>> You know, mamas gotta hang
together.
>> That's right. (both laugh)
>> Okay, now we're playing
Stupid Survivor because this
makes zero sense.
Like, she clearly is not an
athletic person.
I'm so confused.
Like, don't you want to win
immunity?
>> PROBST: All right,
interesting so far.
>> Go, moms.
>> Uh, the tall farmer-looking
boy.
(laughter)
>> Hey, I'm Marcus.
>> Marcus, welcome aboard.
>> I'm going to go for the
surfer dude.
He looks beefy strong.
>> Matty.
>> Hey, Matty.
>> Come on down, Matty!
>> We need some strength, Ace.
>> PROBST: What do you think,
Matty?
You like this tribe?
>> Yeah. (all laugh)
>> Like he has a choice.
>> I got three moms.
>> That's right.
>> PROBST: All right, Marcus,
your choice.
>> I'll take the guy in the
suit.
>> I'm Charlie.
>> PROBST: Charlie's happy.
>> Hi!
>> I'm gonna go with the guy
in the flowered shirt.
>> Randy.
>> PROBST: Randy.
>> Palomo.
>> Paloma.
>> Paloma. Come on down.
>> That's cool.
>> We gotta have a tie on our
team. Come on.
Dan, Dan. Nice to meet you.
>> My lady, Kelly.
>> Yay!
>> I'm taking the young Jay-Z
there on the end.
>> Hey, my name is Danny,
by the way, but you can call me
G-Sizzle or GC.
>> I'm gonna take the other
blond.
I think we need three blonds.
>> PROBST: Three people left.
GC, it's your choice.
>> I'm gonna pick the big homey
with all the game right there.
I don't know your name.
>> Oh, my name is Ken.
>> Ken, my bad. All right, Ken.
>> Come on over, Ken.
>> PROBST: Two choices left.
Jacquie, who do you want on
your tribe?
>> The girl in the suit.
>> Corinne.
>> PROBST: Corinne joins the
yellow tribe.
>> Welcome, Corinne.
>> PROBST: Gotta ask you,
Michelle, last one chosen.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: What does it feel
like?
>> I'll learn to love you guys,
maybe.
>> We'll take another hot girl
over here. That's fine.
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah! Yeah!
>> Finally!
>> PROBST: All right, we have
our two tribes.
Red tribe, you are Fang.
Here are your buffs.
Yellow, you are Kota.
>> Kota!
>> PROBST: All right, guys,
ready to get to your first
challenge?
On my go, you're going to race
through the flags to the top
of the hill, where you will find
two individual immunity idols,
one for each tribe.
The first person from
each tribe to get to the top of
the hill and grab the idol will
be safe at the first Tribal
Council.
Also waiting for you at the top
of the hill are the essentials
that you're gonna start with,
including a bag of rice.
There is one more twist to this
challenge.
Also waiting at the top of the
hill is an extra bag of corn
and beans.
The first entire tribe to get
all of their members across the
black line wins the corn and
beans.
Do you race out ahead selfishly
and get that idol for yourself
or do you work together, thus
ensuring food?
I'll see you at the top.
Survivors ready?
Go!
What are they gonna do?
(women laughing)
GC's out in front.
Gillian bringing up the rear.
Fang quickly falling behind.
Matty and Dan now going back to
help their tribe.
>> Gotta get 'em on the hill.
Gotta get 'em on the hill.
>> PROBST: GC first to the
hill.
>> Come on, guys.
Almost there.
Keep pushing.
>> PROBST: GC and Marcus
looking out for themselves,
going after that individual
immunity.
Big move to make early in the
game.
>> Come on.
Keep it going.
(Paloma grunts)
>> PROBST: Bob helping out
Paloma for Kota.
Ace pushing her.
Marcus first to the top.
Marcus has the idol for Kota.
Here comes GC for Fang.
Michelle right on his tail.
The rest of Fang lagging behind.
For Fang, GC grabs the idol.
Michelle, the last woman
picked, is the first woman
across.
>> Really don't think the
Fang tribe really is that smart.
I was the last one picked, and
I was the first girl up there,
so they can kiss my ass.
>> PROBST: Big question now:
which tribe gets the food?
>> Oh.
>> Come on, girl.
>> Come on, Kota!
Let's go!
Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Kota with a big
lead heading for that food.
>> Come on, guys!
>> Let's go. Let's go.
>> PROBST: Susie, Gillian,
Crystal really struggling for
Fang.
This isn't even close.
Everybody got to be across
the black line.
(Gillian grunts)
(applause)
>> We got it.
>> PROBST: Kota wins the extra
food!
Bag of corn and beans.
Matty just trying to get his
tribe to the top.
>> I think we're screwed in a
lot of physical challenges
because Gillian is going to be
a huge, huge, huge load to
carry.
She's a slow-moving human being.
>> Sorry.
>> Thank you.
>> I know I can run.
But climbing that hill was so
hard.
I had on a dress, and on top of
that, my two shoes weigh at
least ten pounds.
>> That's it.
That's it, Gillian.
>> Good job.
Come on, girl.
Almost, you're almost finished.
>> PROBST: Fang finally crosses
the finish line.
All right, so Marcus has the
idol for Kota.
GC got the idol for Fang.
Kota was the first tribe to get
everybody to the top.
You win the extra bag of corn
and beans.
(applause)
>> PROBST: I got to say, Fang,
if this is any indicator,
it's going to be a long run
for you guys.
That wasn't even close.
All right, Fang, grab your
stuff, including the map, to
your new tribe home.
All right, Kota, grab all your
stuff, including that very
important extra bag of food and
head out.
(elephant trumpeting)
(monkey squawking)
>> Being this far out in nature
in the middle of this huge
jungle is definitely an
unnerving experience.
(monkey squawking)
You don't know what's around
the next tree.
It's really, really scary.
We emerged from the jungle and
we look down and we see the
flag for Kota waving in the
breeze.
There's this beautiful lake,
and in front of it are a couple
of broken-down huts.
(applause)
It was such a joy to see that
there was some shelter kind of
established.
>> It's crazy.
>> It's a wild, wild place, and
you don't want to be out there
exposed to animals.
I mean, the rest of the tribe
could be sitting there and we
could be getting eaten by a
leopard and no one would know
the difference.
>> We have the canoe.
>> We have a dock.
That's awesome.
>> I love it.
I'm excited.
This place looks beautiful.
(laughs)
But there's really wild animals
out here.
(laughs)
This is really Africa.
So I'm not going to get in the
water right now, and I'm not
going to be bathing or swimming
in the lake with my tribe mates.
(laughs)
>> Hey, we need to work on the
roof.
>> It's about to rain.
>> I'm feeling sprinkles.
>> Okay, let's pass these out
now.
>> We got to layer it up.
>> Okay, okay.
>> We're pretty solid.
>> Do you need more twine?
>> Just give me a piece, like, a
foot long.
>> Ugh, Bob-- he's just like the
forever Boy Scout.
>> Go, Bob.
Go, Bob.
Let's give him some moral
support.
>> Bob, he's totally like, he
gets it together.
He's got the camp running really
smoothly.
>> Yeah, it's looking really
good, man.
>> He's 57 years old, and he's
awesome.
>> Good job, guys.
(applause)
>> Whoo!
>> I've done a lot of stuff
around camp.
To me, it's common sense.
I come from Maine.
You know, that's what we do in
Maine.
>> ...exactly together.
>> ...actually use a short
piece of something.
>> It's actually turning out to
be a nice-looking bench.
>> This is the coolest stuff.
>> You're the coolest, Bob.
>> I don't like to spend money
on stuff, so I tinker.
If I don't know how to do it, I
go to the library and get the
book, look it up and go do it.
I'm going to make something
like this when I get home.
>> Bob, at what point are we
going to eat?
(laughter)
>> Oh, yeah?
Oh, great.
We got some huts to begin with.
Awesome.
>> This will work.
Yeah, all right, so,
apparently, according to some
people, we sucked today.
I don't think so.
I thought we were awesome.
And I think that's what we need
to do is we've just got to keep
that awesome spirit going.
There's an African word for
"fierce."
It's... bucale!
(all chattering)
>> I don't know if I believe
you on that.
>> All right.
(cheering)
I always try and maintain a
positive attitude, and I just
hope that our tribe, the Fang
tribe, will stay positive.
This is cool.
Hey, this is awesome.
And maybe they'll forget I was
the old broad that fell up the
hill.
(laughs)
Hey, you guys, if anybody finds
any elephant dung, bring it
back.
It burns well.
>> We've been here 20 minutes
and she wants elephant ...
>> Oh, elephant dung.
>> Oh.
>> Isn't that interesting?
Obviously, one has to be wary.
There are elephants around
because there was elephant dung
that we walked over.
But let's hope that they just
keep their distance.
And if we can get fire going, it
will certainly keep animals
from coming around the camp.
So you want to see the elephant
dung?
>> Not really.
>> It's very interesting.
Look.
>> You want to see my dung?
It's interesting, too.
>> They poop out the seeds that
they don't digest.
And we were wondering, maybe
there might be something edible
inside still.
>> Oh, don't even think about
that.
>> This is our first day, and
I've come to the conclusion
that Gillian is annoying.
>> You can.
You can squeeze elephant dung
and drink it.
>> She is so busy at just
trying to look busy, and she's
not accomplishing crap.
>> You know, here.
>> I know.
>> Kick it open.
>> They're in there.
You want, you want to be the
first to try a termite?
>> You don't have to cook them,
right?
You can just eat them.
>> You just eat them.
I found a queen one.
This is a lot of protein.
As a professional gamer, there
is a stereotype that, you know,
you're antisocial, you're a
nerd, and you sit in your
basement all the time.
And of course, I mean, girls
don't dig that.
Are you going to eat it?
Are you really going to eat it?
It'll be hot if do you that.
Everything that...
You ate it?
How'd it taste?
>> I don't know.
I just swallowed it.
>> You got some protein.
>> I just ate a termite.
>> That was hot.
>> My God, I just ate a termite!
(laughs)
>> Back home, I am very shy with
the girls that I like.
Last girl I kissed was
actually in high school.
That was, like, four, five years
ago, which is a long time.
That was the queen termite.
That wasn't any ordinary
termite.
>> I know, you gave me
something special there.
Like, seriously...
>> Yeah, that was my gift to
you.
>> Thank you.
>> But being here in Gabon with
a girl that, you know, you are
attracted to is a very special
moment in life.
I mean, I am single, and she is
single.
You never know.
A romance could start.
>> It tasted like chocolate.
(Ken mutters)
>> We've got the cantinas right
now.
Why don't we try and do all the
other stuff, get a great camp,
and then we'll work on getting
the water and fire.
>> Um, just from personal need,
where are we going to put the
latrines?
>> Do you guys want us to dig,
like, a three-foot, like, thing?
>> No, not a deep hole.
>> So then what are we doing?
Does everybody individually dig
their own hole, poop, and then
cover it up?
>> The Roman legions used to
do it...
The latrine moves.
So we cut down, we cut down a
foot, and then we cover it up.
And when it's completely flat
again, we move the latrine.
I don't want to punish you guys.
I mean, I'll go do it.
>> I don't mind doing the
latrine.
I'm just confused on how to do
it.
>> I'm the full package.
I'm not just a physical
competitor.
I'm a mental competitor.
I have no fear of being the
sole survivor.
I have no fear of standing in
front of Jeff and expecting my
check for a million dollars.
What I've done at the moment is
give suggestions, let other
people carry them out, take
some of the benefit, and then
they go, "But you know who
suggested that, right?
Ace."
Why don't we go into two groups
and get some really dry wood and
try and do the fire thing?
>> Ace, he's like charismatic,
and I think he has a plan.
Like, he's here to play hard.
I think the best strategy right
now is to just lay low.
>> Our best bet is probably to,
like, let Ace run the show for
a while.
My prediction is Ace is going
to get obnoxious.
Like, let's sort of let him, if
he can, dig his own grave for a
while.
>> People say you don't need
friends here, but if you can
find a friend or someone you
trust, I think that's, like, it
means a lot.
And, like, I was like, I'll
either be playing this game
alone or find someone who I have
a connection with.
I feel that I have a special
bond with Marcus.
Ever since I saw him on the mat
and he picked me, I just felt
this connection in his deep,
blue, beautiful eyes.
>> Do you think I had any doubt
that you're a well-balanced
human being-- like, I wouldn't
be talking to you like this if I
did, so...
>> Okay, cool.
All right.
It feels good to, like, trust
one person at least.
>> Yeah.
The thing with Charlie is I
think he's attracted to me.
But, you know, I'll be honest.
Like, I don't see any romance
with Charlie and I.
I think he's a great guy.
You know, I can see that he's
handsome and smart and all
those things, and I really
can appreciate that about him,
um, but it's not really the way
I roll.
>> You're a nice guy, and you
know it.
>> Yeah, I'm chill, that's all.
I'm straight, so we're in
Eden, but there's no two Adams
here.
(both chuckle)
(trumpeting)
>> Don't they have more bears
than...
>> Shh, there it is!
There it is.
>> You guys hear that?
>> What is that?
>> Sounds like something
calling.
(trumpeting)
>> There it was again.
(elephant trumpeting)
>> The animals are starting to
lurk around camp.
There's an elephant 30 yards
from our house, just cruising
through the forest right behind
our little huts, so it's a
little bit frightening.
(elephant trumpeting)
>> Shh, shh, shh.
(rustling)
>> Ow!
>> Oh, no!
>> I think I have a small
scratch.
>> See it?
>> Holy crap.
>> I was walking back to camp
and I was kneeling down to get
into our little house and I hit
my head on a sharp branch.
The second I hit my head, I felt
the blood running down my face.
I don't know how bad it is.
All I know is it's bleeding a
hell of a lot.
Nurse, do you know anything
about scratches?
>> Well, hmm.
Sorry, can't see a thing.
>> It was totally dark around
here.
>> There I am, this nurse in the
dark.
A real clinical challenge for me
and everybody's looking at me
like I'm going to be able to do
something about it.
Yeah, right.
>> Right.
>> At the risk of being like a
mother, you've got to really
take care of yourself out here.
Just be careful; otherwise,
you're going to get hurt.
So, we've called the medical to
come and take a look at it.
>> You can use that anesthesia
any time you want.
A .22 gauge needle.
It's going to sting, Randy.
>> Break up the monotony of our
first night here.
>> You'll feel a sharp sting.
My suspicion is you're going to
need a few stitches there.
>> Just a couple?
>> Yeah, yeah.
You okay?
>> The cut is smarting a little
bit.
No need to stop; just go for it.
>> Yeah, get it done.
All right?
>> Just so I stay in the game.
I can live with the scar.
I couldn't see it.
I don't have eyes on the top of
my head.
I didn't know if it was three
stitches or 30 stitches.
I knew it was bleeding a lot.
But leaving this game is not an
option.
And I am petrified that this
injury could take me out of the
game.
(trumpeting)
>> You hungry?
Man, we've got some good food.
>> Yeah, we got some...
>> Like what?
>> Grasshoppers and crickets
and...
>> Eww.
>> Who wants them?
>> You might want them.
>> I'm full.
(laughter)
Last night, I cut my head.
The doctors were great.
I think it only took, like, two
or three stitches.
I don't know.
And they put this huge bandage
on it.
But it's better today than it
was yesterday, which means it
will be fine in a couple days.
>> I'm supposed to be on the
frigging equator.
Where the hell is the sun?
Seriously, like, I'm just
freezing.
>> Look at her.
She's miserable.
>> Think you'll be...
>> It's really, really, really
cold at night.
And I'm really bony, so I'm
sleeping bone on wood, and I
don't have any, like, cushion,
so nights are definitely the
hardest.
>> You got some fire?
>> No.
>> Bone is pretty hard, isn't
it?
>> Not hard enough to create
spark.
>> No.
>> You don't think?
I don't think that's going to
work.
>> Trying to make fire with a
bone.
I don't think I got stuck with
the brightest bunch, that's for
sure.
I just kind of keep thinking
"Why did I get stuck with all
these people and the other
team's got all, like, these
smart, beautiful people, and I'm
stuck with these dorks?"
>> Where is the tree mail?
There it is.
Our first tree mail.
>> Let's bring it back.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's bring it back to camp.
>> Okay, let's do it.
>> Okay.
"You've had a cold, dark night
in the jungle, and your
situation is feeling dire.
Wouldn't you love some
security and a nice, big roaring
fire?
>> Yeah!
>> "Well, you'd better move
together for a chance to win the
flame.
If you're not the first to
finish, you may be the first to
leave the game."
>> All right, so we're going to
do a little combined meditation.
So, focus on something.
Hands up.
Going into this challenge,
I wanted us all to be, like,
really in sync, so I felt a
little yoga would really sort
of clean out our humors, get
our energy flowing; the chakras
would be all in tine.
And just get us excited and
motivated for this next
challenge.
Just breathe into it if you feel
any sort of shudder.
(snickers)
>> I should be stretching too.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's challenge, six tribe
members will be belted together.
You will race through a swamp,
over a net wall, under and over
a series of hitching posts.
You'll then dig up three bags
of puzzle pieces...
and make your way to the finish
where the three remaining
tribe members will use those
pieces to solve the puzzle.
First tribe to solve the puzzle
wins.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> Immunity.
>> Immunity!
>> PROBST: This is the most
important thing in this game.
When you have immunity, you
cannot be voted out.
Without it, you are vulnerable.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Winning tribe wins
immunity and fire in the form of
flint.
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Losers go to Tribal
Council, where somebody will be
the first person voted out of
this game.
Going to give you a minute to
strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, so it's Paloma,
Sugar, and Bob solving the
puzzle for Kota.
For Fang, it is Susie, Gillian,
and Randy.
For immunity and fire,
survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, Kota!
>> Go!
>> First leg is through a
leech-filled swamp.
>> Kota! Kota!
>> Neck and neck through the
swamp.
>> Kota!
>> Push it!
Push it!
>> PROBST: Kota with a bit of a
lead.
>> Go!
>> Go, Kota!
>> Go on! Keep moving it!
>> PROBST: Go! Keep it moving!
Everybody's got to get over!
Corrine and Kelly are stuck.
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Fang now in the lead!
>> Yeah, let's go, Fang!
>> Good job, guys!
>> PROBST: Got to go under, then
over.
Fang at the lead at the
crawl-under.
Kota right behind.
>> Go, Fang!
>> PROBST: Do not slow down
here.
Fire and immunity.
You don't want to go to Tribal
Council.
>> You got it! You made it! Go!
>> PROBST: Fang still with the
lead!
>> Come on, Kota!
>> PROBST: Looking for three
bags of puzzle pieces.
Got a friendly exchange of dirt
going on.
It's not a playground.
Million-dollar game.
>> Whoo!
>> Two more, two more.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Kota has their first
bag of puzzle pieces.
>> Come on, y'all.
We got to get some fire for
real.
>> Keep digging!
>> I got a bag.
It's here.
Come on.
>> PROBST: Fang finds their
first bag.
>> You got to pull it out.
Pull it out!
>> PROBST: Just got to get it
out of the dirt.
Kota has their second bag of
puzzle pieces.
Fang still trying to get that
first bag out.
Kota looking for one more bag
before they move on.
Kota has their third and final
bag of puzzle pieces.
They're heading out.
Fang still trying to find the
remaining two bags.
Exhaustion is setting in.
>> Come on, guys. Help us.
>> Let's go, guys.
>> Try and get the sand off.
Don't throw it back in.
>> PROBST: Let's go, Fang.
Keep digging!
You're still in it!
(cheering)
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Get on the mat!
Go!
Start solving it.
>> I teach physics, so I was all
excited to do the puzzle.
It's like working in the
classroom.
>> PROBST: Solve it one bag at a
time, one puzzle at a time.
>> Come on, Fang!
You're not out of it yet!
>> Got it! Got it! Got it!
>> Come on, guys, right here.
>> PROBST: Kota has the first
third of their puzzle solved.
Two bags left.
>> You're fine! Keep going!
>> Okay, these two go together.
>> Kota on their last part of
the puzzle now.
This challenge is an absolute
blowout at this point.
>> Dig fast! Dig!
>> PROBST: It might be time to
put it in the deep freeze,
Gillian.
You might be out of it.
>> Nothing's gone till it's
gone.
>> I'm really tired of that
accent.
I understand "never quit", but
dude, we lost.
>> Come on, guys!
Keep going!
It's not over till it's over!
>> Fang, let's go! Come on!
>> You're okay!
>> PROBST: Fang coming around
the corner, but it's too late.
Kota wins immunity and fire!
(cheering)
>> Boy, that was brutal.
>> PROBST: All right, well, so
far, three days in, this is not
even close.
Two absolute blowouts.
Kota, congratulations.
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Immunity, nobody
going home tonight.
Also, the other half, fire in
the form of flint.
Fang, the only thing I have for
you is a date with me tonight
at Tribal Council, where one of
you will be going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
(trumpeting)
>> Good job, you guys.
>> We did not get destroyed.
>> All right, awesome.
>> And we are not unorganized.
>> We were winning till the
third quarter.
>> Okay, guys.
>> We lost another challenge.
We could have had fire tonight,
and most importantly, we could
have kept our tribe together.
>> We need somebody, and none of
us want to do it, step up and
say, "I'm leader."
>> I'm the only one who is not
worried about getting voted off
because I did win that first
immunity challenge.
And it feels good, but at the
same time, there is nobody
stepped up as a leader of the
tribe.
So, we got to have some kind of
game plan.
>> What are you hearing,
anything?
>> Yeah, Michelle.
>> Why is our team better
without Michelle?
>> Because right now we're...
>> I'm not arguing with you.
>> ...we're in a down-and-out
position; we need positivity.
She's negative; she doesn't want
to be here; she's miserable.
>> I'm up in the air.
I'll do whatever.
>> Michelle.
>> Michelle. Michelle.
>> That's a good reason...
>> You know what, you do what
you think you got to do.
That's who I'm gonna go with.
>> That's who I'm going for.
As of now, I'm voting Michelle.
>> Just let me know where you're
at-- I'm there.
>> Me, too.
>> Are you guys feeling me or
no?
Randy, you look like you're not
feeling me good.
>> It's early.
I'm-I'm... I hear you.
>> It's not that early.
>> If I believed that Michelle
was getting five, six, seven,
eight votes tonight, I'd have no
problem voting for her.
It's just, I don't buy it yet.
>> Hot.
>> Get out of the sun, then.
>> I would prefer Gillian to go
tonight, just because... she's a
60-year-old woman.
Nothing against the
60-year-old women out there,
but don't come to my camp.
>> You guys were great.
You just had to dig differently,
and that's all.
>> I didn't think about that.
>> So just because it seems
like we're disorganized, I don't
think any of us think we are.
>> She cheerleads and blows
sunshine, thinking they're gonna
like her, but, to be honest,
Gillian is worthless, totally
worthless.
>> So, who's leaving tonight?
>> I really want to... want to
vote out Gillian.
>> That's what I was thinking.
She's the oldest and would slow
us down the most.
>> Gillian is our weakest
member, like, in everything, and
we do need physical players
right now.
Like, she's a nice lady, but I
don't think she's meant for this
game.
I don't know how everybody else
is gonna vote.
I think you're on the outs right
now.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. I mean, we're the...
>> That's so funny 'cause that
would just, like, confirm my
belief in this tribe that
they're, like, the dumbest
people on earth.
>> You don't talk to anybody
besides me, so they do think...
>> They're all retarded. Like...
>> I know.
I would really rather keep
Michelle in this tribe because
I really do like Michelle, and I
really do think that she would
be allies with me.
>> It's hard for me to pretend
to like people that... really
frustrate me.
>> I seriously don't know what's
gonna go on at Tribal Council
tonight.
I think it's gonna be a mixed
vote.
>> She's Negative Nancy.
>> And there will be no
hesitation in me tonight to vote
Michelle off for that whole
reason.
>> Me, neither.
>> She's-she's sad.
She just doesn't need to be
here.
I personally had absolutely no
qualms about myself voting for
Michelle.
I'm sorry, but I think Michelle
needs to go home, for her sake
and for our sake.
She's just having too hard a
time, and it's not good for all
of us.
Bad vibes is just not a good
thing to have around.
I might be the naive woman
that's just walking around
thinking, "Tra-la, it's not me,
thank God," um, but it may be.
Uh, I doubt it, though.
I really feel Michelle just
doesn't want to be here.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Grab a torch, approach a flame,
dip it in, and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire, you
are still in the game.
When your fire's gone, so are
you.
That will be the case for one of
you tonight.
Well, let's just get right into
it.
Dan, let me ask you how you guys
think you did at today's
immunity challenge.
>> I think we did okay.
I think we did... I think we did
better than we expected.
>> PROBST: You think you did
okay.
>> I do.
>> PROBST: So in addition to
being a complete disaster, this
tribe is in total denial.
>> I disagree.
I don't think it was a complete
and utter disaster.
I think we can take those guys,
and, uh, we're looking forward
to the next challenge.
>> PROBST (chuckles): 'Kay.
Michelle, give me the
play-by-play.
You were in there.
What was going on?
>> Well, it took a long time,
and there were people taking
breaks.
Uh, Ken was taking a break.
G-Sizzle resting on his bag
digging with one hand.
>> I'm-I'm sorry. I got tired.
I mean, I got exhausted, so,
yeah, I took a break.
If that was the reason we lost,
I'm sorry, but, I mean...
>> Well, it wasn't the reason we
won 'cause we're sitting here.
>> You can't go a hundred
percent, a hundred percent of
the time.
>> Um, that's what a challenge
is, that's what a race is.
You don't stop till the job is
done.
>> Oh, for Pete's sake, then why
didn't you step up at that
point and just get right on it?
>> I didn't stop digging.
>> But you should've verbalized
it.
You should've said, "Hey, will
you do this?"
>> That's what I was doing.
"Come on, y'all, hustle!"
>> All right, all right, you're
right.
(several talking at once)
>> There was a barrier there, so
we could not see you guys.
>> I just thought it's common
sense that, you know, when we're
in a race that you don't stop
until we're done or we win.
>> PROBST: Well, I'll tell you
what I just saw.
I asked a simple question, and
immediately you guys went into
arguing about something else.
So, Crystal, who's leading this
tribe?
>> Right now, at this current
moment, we don't have a distinct
leader.
It's frustrating.
>> PROBST: Gillian, you started
picking this tribe.
Are you happy with the fact that
you still don't have any
leadership?
>> I think there are plenty
leaders in the group, but I
think that a lot of people feel
like it's kind of the death
knell to... to come out as the
leader.
>> PROBST: Anybody willing to
step up and say, "I think I
could help us avoid coming to
Tribal Council"?
Anybody willing?
>> I think it would be a good
idea if we had someone who we
all looked up to and said, "You
could definitely be the leader
of our tribe," but since none of
us have that feeling toward...
>> I think you could.
>> I happen to think you could,
too.
>> I think it needs to be
discussed.
(several talking at once)
>> As long as they're open to
the eight other soldiers'
opinions or strategies, I think
you got a great style.
>> I appreciate you guys saying
that, but maybe I don't have the
courage to be the leader
because I don't want to lead you
in the wrong direction and have
you upset with me for... for
making that decision.
But if I was volunteered, I'll
take it.
If they want me to roll with it,
I mean, I'll do it.
>> PROBST: GC's willing to be
the leader.
Who's in favor of that?
>> I didn't say that, either.
I said if they wanted me to...
>> PROBST: GC is open to being
the leader if you would like him
to be.
>> I'll give you the answer now.
Yes, I would vote for GC to be
the leader.
>> PROBST: Randy.
>> Good luck.
>> PROBST: Gillian, you
all right with GC?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: How about you,
Michelle?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Ken.
>> He would be the best
candidate.
>> PROBST: How about you, Susie?
>> I'm good with that.
>> PROBST: Matty?
>> I'm fine with that.
>> PROBST: We accomplished
something big.
I'm impressed.
Fang has a leader, and his name
is GC.
Good.
Let's talk about relationships.
Michelle, who are you closest to
out here?
>> Probably... Ken.
We're both the youngest, and
we were both the last picked.
I like talking to him the most.
>> PROBST: How much does it
weigh on you that you were the
last person picked?
>> I kind of wasn't surprised,
but I think that in the first
challenge, I proved myself very
worthy of being in any tribe,
and I definitely think there's
some deadweight that we could
throw off the boat that would
make us a little stronger, a
little faster.
>> PROBST: Gillian, on the
flip side, you struggled in that
first challenge.
>> Well, I saw the challenge,
and I thought, "I'm dead."
Yeah, it sucked, and I was.
I'm the old bag that had to be
helped up by two young bucks up
the hill.
But, you guys, thank you.
But I hope that everybody's been
able to see that there's
actually more to me than just
the gray hair and the old woman
that sucked on the hill.
>> PROBST: All right, it's time
to get to the vote.
GC, you have the immunity
necklace.
As always, you can give it to
somebody else if you want to or
keep it for yourself.
>> I'm going to go ahead and
rock this for tonight.
I'll roll with it.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
GC.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Matty, you're up.
♪ ♪
>> I think you're the weakest on
this tribe.
That's pretty much it.
♪ ♪
>> I don't think you want to be
here.
And with your whole attitude
about everything, I don't think
you should be.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
♪ ♪
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Counsel area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote... Michelle.
Gillian.
One vote Michelle;
one vote Gillian.
Michelle.
Two votes Michelle;
one vote Gillian.
Michelle.
Three votes Michelle;
one vote Gillian.
Michelle.
That's four votes Michelle;
one vote Gillian.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon: Michelle.
That's five; that's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
Michelle, the Tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
♪ ♪
Well, you came in here as a
group of individuals.
It seems like you found the
necessary leadership to leave
here as a tribe.
More good news: you'll be
taking your torches with you
back to camp, which means you
will have fire.
(cheering)
>> Thank you, God!
>> PROBST: Here's your flint.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
>> Thank you, Jeff!
>> PROBST: Good night.
>> We're gonna eat some rice!
♪ ♪
(trumpeting)
>> Ow! Baby!
Oh, yeah.
Another day in Gabon.
Michelle's gone.
Oh, man, that was rough.
We had our first Tribal
Council tonight, and it sucked.
We lost Michelle, and we were
lucky enough to get flint
tonight.
>> So Kenny, you want to do the
honors?
Or how are you feeling?
>> Me? I can do the fire
if you want.
>> Yes, I think you should do
the fire.
Yeah, he should do it.
>> And there should be no
pressure, but as our leader, you
miss fire, and you're getting
voted out.
>> Tonight, to my surprise, my
tribe picked me to be the
leader of the tribe.
It kind of feels good that
people want me to be the leader
of the tribe, but at the same
time, I feel like I'm going to
have a bigger target on my back
just because of that title.
>> There it is. Don't stop!
Got it.
Okay, don't stop. Keep it going.
Yep, fire, fire, fire!
>> It's going good.
Throw it over.
>> GC is the hero.
>> Team captain once again.
>> It feels good tonight just
knowing that I'm the one who got
the fire started and my tribe is
now able to eat and we're gonna
be warm.
>> He's excited. He's got fire.
>> It's sparking right now.
It's cracking.
The fire is cracking.
I'm feeling good.
♪ ♪
>> Today, things are
going fairly well.
I think the tribe settled down
a lot after the, the great
victory we had yesterday, and
we're kind of doing the daily
chores.
>> I love our team.
Our team rocks!
(laughter)
>> Rice pudding?
Oh, thank you. Very nice.
>> Marcus is, like, my favorite
person out here.
He's funny. He's smart.
He's athletic.
He's, like, the whole package.
And I can't understand
why a million girls aren't
jumping all over him because I
certainly would be if I could.
>> And away we go.
(bird cooing)
We have a lot to talk about,
I think.
I can't stress enough how safe
I feel because I have you
because when you go off, like, I
do get this, like, pang of
(gasps), you know?
And, like, when I see that
you're there, it's like even
though I'm not there, like, I
feel like, I'm there in spirit,
and I'm, like, yeah, like,
someone's gonna back me up
if I'm, like, knocked down.
Our alliance is, like,
clearly...
I just can't imagine
there being a stronger one.
>> I think you just have to see
how every day it stacks up and
gets stronger and stronger.
I kind of have this inner circle
bond with Charlie.
I look at it like layers of an
onion.
And I think Charlie's
the guy that's sort of the
innermost layer, then we're
adding people as we go along.
I, I talked to Jacquie a little
bit, you know?
She seems like a really cool
girl.
And I am totally psyched
'cause I know she likes you.
Like, I think Jacquie might get
along.
>> I think at this point, it's
looking like the large onion
alliance, as I might call it:
myself, Charlie, Jacquie,
Corinne, is what we're shooting
for.
Jacquie is an awesome girl and
I think she's also very
intelligent.
And I think Corinne is probably
the smartest one around.
>> I think the best way to
strategize with her is to get
to know her as a person, like...
>> Yeah.
I'm gonna talk to Corinne
and kind of get a vibe for her
'cause no one's really made any
official pitch at this point.
(buzzing)
>> If we're going to go look for
some fruit or something, I think
it'll be best to do it before it
gets too hot.
Susie and Crystal, would y'all
mind getting fruit?
Fruit.
Yeah, Matty, maybe you and Randy
could find stuff that we could
use maybe as spoons or bowls or
something.
>> Okay.
>> You know, you get sticks,
kind of like, like, uh...
>> Shape 'em.
>> Yeah, shape 'em and mix
foods.
>> Kenny, if you want to just,
man, grass or anything, just
stuff we might could use for a
good layer.
Being the leader right now, I
think, is working out okay.
I'm just trying to get this camp
put together.
I'm a maintenance supervisor,
you know, and it's my job to
build things and get them put
together.
I'm like, man, let's just get
this thing together and let's
get this ball rolling.
>> If you guys want the best
bedding, we'd have to weave.
>> At least put down a layer of
grass, and whatever you're
talking about weaving, we can
put on top of that.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> So that way, at night we're
all comfortable.
>> I guess I can weave all day.
>> Let's do it.
>> All right, you ready?
>> Yeah.
So far, the ideas that I present
to 'em they think are pretty
good, so we've got a plan for
the day.
>> We're gonna have to change
out this water.
>> This is rice water.
>> Actually, do you mind if I
try to make it?
>> What, the rice?
>> Yeah... if you don't mind.
>> No, of course not.
>> If, if you're all ready, I'll
start it now.
>> Yeah, tha-that's what I was
doing.
Just wing it.
If you get too much water, we
just cook it longer and...
>> Okay.
>> GC, you use lake water.
All we have up there is clean
water.
It's boiled.
>> Anything wrong with using
clean water?
>> Yeah, to make rice you got to
boil it again, and that doesn't
make sense.
Boil it once and use lake water.
>> What do you mean we have to
boil it twice?
It's already boiled.
It's just water.
Do you understand what I'm
saying?
>> I understand what you're
saying, but you're doing the
work twice.
>> It's just water, Randy.
We're surrounded by water, bro.
>> I get you.
>> Our tribe has a leader-- GC--
but he's too young and he
doesn't know squat about any of
this, and my new operation is
called Operation Let Other
People Crash and Burn.
>> Didn't you want us to go get
fruit?
>> We're going to get leaves for
the bed.
>> What's happening?
What's cracking?
Ain't nobody moving.
>> My best plan right now is
just to keep my mouth shut, sit
on my ass, and watch us
self-destruct.
>> The king is restless this
morning.
(monkeys squealing)
>> I only talked to Jacquie.
>> Oh, really?
>> For me, at least, I'm only
putting my-- I trust Jacquie
wholeheartedly.
She's like my girl, and I trust
you.
>> I like hanging out with you,
and, like, I think it would be
great to have, like, a smaller
layer of the group.
>> Yeah, I think we have a
really good chance.
I would like the alliance to be,
like, me, you, and Jacquie,
tight, strong, Charlie, and then
just have, like, one, like,
like, loser person.
>> I think things are kind of
naturally just going the right
direction.
>> Originally when I came in, I
really liked Jacquie and I
really liked Marcus and also
Charlie 'cause I feel like
they're really trustworthy.
I know that that's only four and
that leaves five out, but that's
a short-term thing.
And then we just need a
peripheral one extra person to
be in the majority, and Bob is
really benign.
Like, everyone likes him.
>> I think Bob's the best,
right?
>> Right.
>> Bob is our chance.
If we can convince Bob that
going with Ace is not the right
way to go, then, like...
>> I can bring Bob in, like,
full-on bring him in.
>> Better situation.
>> The only, only problem is I
don't want to give him too much
information.
>> When Corinne, Marcus,
Jacquie, and I were out in the
forest, it was the first time
we ever talked strategy as a
foursome.
>> If they see us all going off,
they're probably gonna be like--
everyone is going to get
nervous.
>> What should we do?
This is bad business.
Let's go back.
>> It was like magic.
It was like one brain working as
one.
It was amazing.
I really think we're on the same
page here.
♪ ♪
(snoring)
>> Well, I think the morning
started some time when the moon
was right above us.
GC had got up earlier.
I heard this washing machine
going, doing lots of, you know,
the slushy, slushy, slushy
washing machine noises and stuff
like that.
And I thought: just keep it down
so we can all sleep.
Otherwise we're going to be
killed.
>> Damn, I'm sweating like
crazy.
>> I'm sweating like mad, too.
>> And then a second person
joined him, and then the talking
started and more talking,
and more talking, and then
Susie joined them, and then that
got even louder.
(laughter)
>> Dude, you are the king of
snoring.
>> Gillian was letting it out
last night.
>> Was she?
>> I have, I have a request.
I'm going to voice my opinion.
We have all day to blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah.
Perhaps we could just keep it
down for certain times during
the night.
>> I'm sorry, Gill, but I was,
I was woke up, like, early this
morning because five people
were in there snoring.
>> Yeah, I...
>> All right?
So I got up as quietly as I
could.
If other people come out and
start talking, don't come out to
me and say...
>> I didn't say...
>> It felt like, it felt like
when you came out, you were
saying Danny, uh...
>> If I wanted to attack you, I
would have said, "Danny, quit
flapping your gums at night."
>> I'm a grown man.
Ain't nobody gonna tell me
when I can do something and
when I can't.
>> Do you see I didn't tell
you what to do?
>> I'm just telling you.
>> I just asked.
I just put in a request-- could
we keep the blah, blah, blah
down.
>> We don't need a damn leader.
I'm younger than all y'all, so
what I'm being the leader for?
I didn't want to be a leader,
I'm not gonna let y'all force me
to be the leader.
So I'm not going to.
>> GC, which stands for
"golden child," resigned as
leader, which was probably the
best leadership call he's made
since he's been leader because
he hasn't led anything.
>> So, Dan, if you want to step
up, here's your chance.
Randy, you want to step up?
I mean, you guys say-- if that's
what you want, somebody here,
somebody else's chance.
And if nobody says nothing, then
that means we don't need a
leader because obviously
nobody wants to be a leader.
>> He's a leader who quit, who
quit this morning.
It was just the complete
opposite reaction that you
would want from any kind of
leader.
>> If you want to be the
leader, man, I'm telling you...
>> I-I don't necessarily think
my management style would-would
be good for this tribe.
I-I personally don't.
So I-I prefer not to.
Everyone's got their own
management style, you know.
I-I know I-I'm highly emotional.
So I'm not sure my-my management
style would be any better.
I would like to be a silent
leader.
The silent leader is never the
one that gets the blame, but he
gets to lead, so that would be
a great direction.
>> We got mail.
>> Yeah!
>> Hey!
>> Okay, listen, listen, listen.
>> "A rolling stone gathers no
moss, and losers are just left
wishing.
One tribe will have to vote
someone out, the other one will
soon be fishing."
>> We got tree mail this
morning, and I definitely think
we have a chance of winning, but
we'd have a much better chance
if we were more unified.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Oh, there it is.
>> Nice.
>> There it is.
>> I had the idea of painting
people's faces with charcoal,
and that seemed to bring the
mood up a little bit.
>> Yeah, this is my "go to war"
face.
I'm about to tear it up!
>> Oh, that's good.
>> I'm gonna kick your ass!
(laughter)
(elephant trumpeting)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Kota getting your first look at
the new Fang tribe.
Michelle voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
What's with the face paint?
Gillian?
>> Unification.
>> United tribe coming to take
them on, and, uh, do it.
>> PROBST: Guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> ALL: Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
I will take back the immunity
idol.
Thank you, Marcus.
>> See you in a bit.
(scattered laughter)
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, on my go,
both tribes will push a large
boulder through a series of
gates.
Along the way, you must retrieve
two sets of three keys.
When you reach the final gate,
you'll use those keys to open
three locks, then race to the
finish.
First tribe to the finish with
their boulder securely on their
pedestal wins immunity and
reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for on that end?
(all voicing assent)
>> PROBST: Here's your reward.
Fishing gear.
(applause)
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Everything you need
to fish.
You have hooks, line, netting.
You have worms.
Traps.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: And a spear.
>> Oh, we get the business.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will choose one
person from the losing tribe to
go to Exile Island.
Good news, bad news about Exile.
Bad news is, when you're away,
things happen at camp.
You never want to be away from
camp.
Good news-- waiting for you at
Exile Island-- the first clue to
the location of a hidden
immunity idol.
If you have immunity as a tribe
or as an individual, you cannot
be voted out of this game.
Worth playing for?
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Kota, you have one
extra member.
Gonna have to sit somebody out.
Who is it going to be?
>> Me.
>> PROBST: All right, Paloma,
take a seat on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you
a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
For immunity and reward,
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Push.
Push more!
Get on the side!
Get on the side.
>> Susie, Susie.
>> PROBST: These hills are
steep.
You're going to have to dig
deep.
That ball is heavy.
>> Gillian, get out of the way
so somebody else can push.
>> PROBST: Kota with a bit of a
lead.
Fang right behind, no thanks to
Gillian.
Let's go.
>> And then get around it.
>> PROBST: Kota-- first to their
first set of keys.
Fang slowing down right before
they get there.
>> Hold it. Hold it.
>> PROBST: Bob working the
knots for Kota.
>> Let's go.
>> Okay, if you stabilize this.
>> PROBST: Head up top for Fang.
>> Go, Ken!
>> Come on...
>> PROBST: Bob has the keys for
Kota.
They're heading out.
(woman whoops)
>> Go, Ken.
>> PROBST: Ken has the keys for
Fang.
They're heading out.
>> Guys!
>> Yeah!
>> How's it going?
Let's get it over here.
>> Not too much push.
>> Get there...
>> Let's go.
>> PROBST: Kota still with a
bit of a lead heading down the
hill.
(indistinct chatter)
(boulders banging)
Major collision between Kota
and Fang.
>> Aah!
>> Lucky key.
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
>> Got the key.
>> PROBST: We are dead even at
the second set of keys.
>> Up.
>> Okay, you can do it.
>> Good job, Bob.
Don't look at anybody but
yourself.
>> Let's go, Ken.
>> PROBST: Ken working the
knots for Fang.
Bob once again flying through
the knots for Kota.
>> Go.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Kota again is out
first.
>> Nice, Bob.
>> Come on, dude.
>> PROBST: Fang right behind.
We've got a race.
>> Go.
>> Straight.
Right, right, right.
>> We got it, guys.
>> Come on.
Give it all, you guys.
>> Go, go.
(overlapping chatter)
>> Come on!
>> Go, go, go!
>> Yeah, go... go.
>> PROBST: Kota first to the
final gate.
(mumbling)
>> PROBST: Fang now working on
their locks.
>> Come on. Let's go.
>> PROBST: You have six keys,
but only three locks.
The question is, how lucky are
you?
>> Wrong keys.
>> Go, go, go.
Where's the second set?
>> Mine's good.
>> PROBST: Kota has their first
lock undone.
Fang has their first lock.
Kota has their second lock.
Fang now has their second lock
undone.
>> Yes, go!
>> PROBST: Kota has their third
lock.
>> Hold it! Hold it!
Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Kota racing to the
finish.
Fang has their third lock
undone.
It's a race to the finish.
>> Come on. Let's go.
>> Keep going.
Huh?
>> Get ready.
Get on, Charlie.
Go around the other side.
>> Don't stop.
Push up.
>> PROBST: Kota, got to get the
ball on the pedestal in order
to win.
>> Push!
>> Put it up!
>> Go! Everybody on the back
side!
>> PROBST: Fang racing to the
end.
They've still got a shot.
>> Let's get it.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Push.
>> Roll it back a little bit.
Roll it back a little bit.
>> Oh, God.
>> Come on.
>> Good going.
>> Go!
(grunting)
>> You're done.
>> PROBST: Kota wins immunity
and reward.
>> Yay!
(panting)
>> Much different from the last
challenge, guys.
You were right there.
>> Good job, y'all.
It's all right.
(grunting)
>> PROBST: Congratulations,
Kota.
Immunity once again is yours.
In addition, fishing supply.
Now you have a big decision to
make.
Who from the tribe of Fang do
you want to send to Exile
Island?
(whispering)
>> Yup.
Dan.
>> PROBST: Dan.
Going to Exile Island.
Get your stuff.
Straight down, hang a left.
You'll know when to use the map.
You will return in time for
your next Tribal Council.
Fang, once again, you have a
date with me at Tribal Council
tomorrow night, where the second
person will be voted out of this
game.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp, and we'll see you at
Tribal tomorrow.
Kota, congratulations.
Grab your fishing gear.
♪ ♪
(laughing)
>> I was so excited when we won
the fishing gear for our reward.
We are by far the stronger team
in that we've won three
challenges, and we just are
getting stronger and stronger
because of the rewards that we
win.
>> So what do we do first?
Celebrate first?
>> Hakuna matata.
♪ ♪
(humming)
>> Whoa.
>> I sort of expected the worst
out here.
This is 10,000 times better than
my normal life at home.
Like, I'm having a blast out
here.
Like, this is totally fun.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Ooh, real fishing gear.
>> Our morale is up.
Everybody's, like, all about
teamwork, and we have, like, the
most clever guys possible.
They already know how to, like,
put the net out.
We have all of our fishing lines
going.
>> All right, Marcus!
(cheering)
>> Oh, my God.
>> Whoo!
>> We're doing really well.
I don't envision us losing ever.
(giggles)
♪ ♪
>> Fang lost a challenge and the
winning team got to send one of
the losing tribe members to
Exile Island.
I don't think it's a smart move
for Kota to send a strong guy to
go get an immunity idol.
I'm a pretty analytical thinker.
You know, law school does that
to you.
So, I can crack this clue and
I'm going to put in some hard
work and do whatever it takes to
get it done.
"You've arrived in Exile.
A lovely, lonely place in this
Garden of Eden, a difficult
choice you'll face.
One choice provides an apple;
one choice provides direction.
Spend your time in idle comfort
or seek idol protection."
Clue or comfort?
I could choose.
I'm going with clue.
I had chose clue right away, no
questions asked because we're
here for one reason, and that's
the million dollars.
And one night of comfort is not
going to help me get to that.
Let's see what we got here.
"Across the lake you see so well
there lies a sandy crater.
The object hidden in its floor
will surely help you later."
"A sandy crater."
"Across the lake you see so
well."
It's got to be the clearing.
Could be in the lake.
"The object hidden in its floor
will surely help you later."
"A sandy crater."
This place is enormous.
It could be anywhere.
I don't see it coming from here.
Frustrated that I can't beat the
clue.
Frustrated that I'm not smart
enough to find this idol.
Exile Island is officially the
worst place ever.
I don't care what the view is.
These clues play with your mind.
I can't possibly be this stupid
that I'm missing something here.
I should be able to figure this
clue out, and right now, I'm
just miserable.
I'm tired.
I'm thirsty, hungry.
I've got cuts everywhere,
all over my hands.
And I cannot find this immunity
idol.
And I need this immunity idol.
I'm not having any luck.
Sucks.
♪ ♪
>> I don't think anybody should
be depressed about our
performance today?
>> I agree.
I absolutely agree. Listen...
>> We did really well.
>> We did well.
>> I think if you come-- if you
come away from something knowing
you did the best you could, then
that's what counts.
>> We deserve lunch after it,
for damn sure.
>> No, but seriously, it was a
huge improvement.
We didn't get slaughtered.
>> Right, right.
>> Man, we lost another damn
challenge today, for the third
time in a row, and it's
frustrating 'cause, uh, we
really need it, and, you know,
especially the fishing gear.
It's just tough, you know,
having to deal with the losses
over and over again.
You know, it starts to make you
feel like you might not ever
win.
>> Oh, man!
Like on a personal and serious
note, okay.
How do you feel about our tribe?
>> Right now, we're lacking kind
of, like, the physical part.
>> Yeah.
>> Like, today, like, everyone
was doing their job except for
like Gillian.
All the challenges so far here
have been physical.
So we haven't been winning any
challenges because we're losers.
So, you have to learn from your
mistakes that why we lost and
right now the reason why we lost
is Gillian.
At Tribal, I'm putting down
Gill, hands down no matter what.
>> I'm just going to say it out
loud.
"Jeff, I don't even want to walk
to the paper.
Okay?
I'm just going to tell you
right now 'cause I even ain't
got the energy to walk up
there.
Gillian."
>> So you, too, then.
>> Huh?
>> You, too.
>> I don't know if there's any
possibility that, uh, anybody's
interested in kind of looking at
the group and seeing who might
be a surprise vote out at this
stage.
'Cause that could be not a bad
thing because I'll tell you
what, it's the young ones that
are ganging up against us.
>> That's right.
I've seen that, too.
So that could swing both ways.
I'm just kind of wondering
where I'm at.
>> Well, I hate to say it, but
personally, I don't want to see
the-the strongest people go, but
there are some very weak young
people.
>> And who would you take out?
>> I'd go for Kenny first.
>> You'd do Kenny?
>> That's who I would...
>> Sometimes if you think too
much, we're-we're going to dig
ourselves a hole.
>> Well, true, but I really
think we need to start thinking.
Otherwise, we've dug our hole,
we're in it, and the nails are
on the coffin.
You're-you're next.
They'll get rid of me first, but
you're next.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm telling you, they're
going to wipe us out.
>> I know. I know.
>> The possibility is that I
will be booted because I'm a
drag on the team.
At every challenge I'm the
walking target.
I don't just have the target on
my back.
I'm it.
There are a lot of twists down
the road and something could
change.
We've got to start working on
it 'cause otherwise my target's
going to be hit.
♪ ♪
>> Another Tribal Council for us
again tonight because we
haven't won a challenge yet.
There's really nothing we can do
about that right now, but we
have a problem just-just pulling
it together when it-- when it's
crunch time, when it's time to
go.
We're just not making it happen.
We really need something around
this place.
We need a boost.
We're a very needy tribe right
about now.
We need some food more than
anything, probably.
♪ ♪
>> I think this part under the
earpiece here is our best bet,
you know.
This stuff bends pretty easy.
And, shoot, I've got another
half there.
>> Right on, dude.
>> Finally, we came up with a
group effort.
Randy, he's-he's pretty good.
He took his grasses, broke 'em
apart, and made a fishing hook
out of it.
That is beau-ti-ful!
The early hopper catches the
fish.
With his fishing hook and-and my
shoestrings, it's definitely a
group effort.
Like, um, this morning, I think
Crystal, Sue, and maybe even
Gillian, they all went and
looked for worms, and they found
six worms.
>> Oh, I got another!
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah, baby.
>> Everybody's helping, and it's
working out for everybody.
>> Don't worry.
We'll catch a fish.
>> Okay, boys.
>> Okay.
>> Go make Mama proud.
♪ ♪
>> Come on, fishes!
Go for the worm.
Come on, buddy.
You know you want it.
Oh, it's a big one.
>> Oh, it's coming back.
It's coming back.
Seize it.
Okay, pull.
>> Ow!
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Success!
Finally!
We caught some damn fish around
this place.
>> Now, that is meat.
>> We lost reward challenge that
was supposed to get us fishing
gear, but we caught fish anyway.
We don't need that stuff.
We're good.
We're survival experts.
>> We got something.
We got five sardines.
>> Let's see 'em.
>> Got 'em, y'all.
>> We got some sardines.
>> Oh, yes!
Thank you!
>> All right!
>> Thank you!
>> It looks good!
>> Ooh, I can smell 'em.
>> Mmm.
>> Oh, look at that.
>> The Fang Tribe has protein,
finally, after six days now,
and it feels good.
>> Oh, it's Dan coming back.
>> Oh, good.
>> All right.
>> Man's back.
>> All right!
Come on back.
>> It's a bad place.
>> Welcome back.
>> No, but it was not-not fun at
all.
Thank you so much.
>> How was it?
>> Did you have fire?
>> Did you have any food?
>> I can't really talk about it.
>> Oh. Why, it was so bad?
(mumbling)
>> No. I mean, there was a
good...
I just made the bad choice.
>> What?
>> There's, like, a choice when
you get there.
>> Oh.
>> If we have to send one of
their tribe members, we need to
think about it.
>> Yeah.
>> You send a weak player, they
may just quit right there.
>> Yeah.
>> I think a weak player...
>> You send a strong player,
they may find the idol and be
even stronger.
>> True. Plus, a stronger
player...
>> But I don't know if anyone is
going to find that thing.
I looked, like, five or six
hours.
>> I figured. I said, "I bet
Dan's is gonna be going all over
the place looking for that."
>> Couldn't find it.
I was going berserk.
>> Dan's back from Exile Island,
and, uh, he was acting real
strange, man.
Like, I just don't get this guy.
>> Oh, man, it really makes you
rethink, like, your reasons for
doing this.
(laughter)
>> I'm guessing that he-he
either knows where it is, or Dan
has the immunity idol right now.
>> Yeah, something's fishy with
Dan, for sure.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, it is.
>> Fishy.
He either ate, or he's got the
idol.
>> I think Dan is cool.
>> Something's up, dude.
>> If Dan has the immunity idol
right now, it affects my game
because he will hold the power
of the tribe.
>> The two people on the block
right now is Dan or Gillian.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Like-Like 100%...
>> We cannot trust Dan 100%.
>> 50-50.
>> 100%.
>> 50...
>> Yeah.
>> He's definitely got the idol,
dude.
He's acting too weird.
>> (laughing): No...
>> He's too comfortable.
>> He's not tripping out like
normal.
>> I think he's just paranoid.
I think he's just really,
really tired and had a tough
night.
I really do.
>> You don't think he's got it,
dude, you really don't?
>> I really don't.
>> He's coming back.
>> He's a smart person.
I think he has it.
>> He's coming back.
>> Isn't the plan, according to
everybody, Gillian?
>> What?
No. Right now, the way things
seems is, it could be Dan.
>> I'd rather have Gillian go.
>> If you guys decide Dan goes
first, I'm definitely going
with you.
>> We got to weigh our options,
too.
My whole thing is, Dan is smart,
and I think that Dan is going to
try to...
>> He's not smart enough.
>> He's a lawyer.
It takes a person with a certain
swagger to be a lawyer.
Not everybody is cut out to
be lawyers.
(snorts)
>> PROBST: Catch me up on what's
happened in the last few days.
Last time I saw you, you
decided we need a leader.
GC's going to be the leader.
How's it going being the leader?
>> Well, uh, it was...
>> It was?
>> It was going all right for a
day or two, but my group kind of
volunteered me to be the leader,
and that's not a position that I
want to be in in this game with
this tribe.
And I told them, you know, I
don't want to be the leader of
the group.
>> PROBST: Susie, what happened?
>> There was a little conflict
between Gillian, I think.
She just wanted to voice her
opinion about something, and GC
felt like he was being attacked.
So, that's kind of what
happened.
It kind of just fell apart.
>> And it definitely doesn't
mean I'm not helping out.
It doesn't mean I'm not giving
my opinion.
It doesn't mean we're not
working together as a group.
It just means that I'm not the
one that everybody is looking to
for some kind of guidance, which
some people just really don't
need anyway.
>> PROBST: Randy, what's the
problem right now with the
tribe?
>> We've got eight individuals.
Period.
I see where GC is coming from.
I wouldn't want to lead this
bunch, either.
>> PROBST: Dan, is the problem
that there's just too many
disruptive forces?
I'm up; you're down?
I'm left; you're right?
>> I think it's lack of
leadership.
And I can understand that you
don't want to be voted off for
standing up.
I mean, you just kind of made a
face and shook your head when I
said that, but that's no
different than what Randy just
said.
>> And I was, like, "If you
really feel like we need a
leader, how about somebody else
step in, wants to be that
person?"
And what did everybody do?
>> PROBST: Crystal, are you
frustrated that you don't have
a leader?
>> It can be a little bit
frustrating, but sometimes, our
day-to-day chores at the house,
we don't need a leader.
If we see the wood is going
low, somebody is going to get
up.
But when it's time to go to
war, Jeff, I'm all about in the
zone.
I need to hear about how we're
going to get our heads together
and how we're going to kick
Kota's butt.
>> I agree there.
It's the strategies and the
discipline and the challenges
that we need to pull together
on, and we all need to agree.
Otherwise, we're doomed.
>> PROBST: GC, tell me about
camp life.
Has it gotten any better?
>> It got a little bit better,
man, 'cause, uh, the homie Randy
right here made us a fishing
hook.
Crystal and Sue, and I think
Gill even, were out getting
worms this morning.
And me and Kenny hopped on the
boat, and we caught, like, five
fish.
They were small, but, hey, it
helped out a lot.
It made us feel a lot better.
>> PROBST: Dan, tell me about
Exile Island.
>> It's a... It's a tough place.
I mean, it's a good opportunity,
but it can really mess with your
mind a little bit.
Searching for that idol comes
with its price because you
could spend all day looking for
the idol and not find it.
So, it can play that trick on
you a little bit, being out
there.
>> PROBST: Matt, are you at all
concerned over whether Dan may
have found the hidden immunity
idol already?
>> Yeah, there's a little
concern.
>> PROBST: Crystal, did you guys
talk about it?
>> You know we did!
(laughter)
Okay, it's bound to happen.
Yes, we talked, and I think Dan
is a very smart gentleman.
And I think you got the idol.
(laughing): That's just my
thing.
I think you found it.
But, you know, as limited... as
limited clues...
>> I don't see any idol in
there, sister.
>> It's fine.
It's limited clues.
>> I-I don't lie.
I just don't lie.
>> I don't discount anyone or
anytng in this gam
>> I don't have the idol.
I wish I did.
So don't try and flush it out,
please!
I don't want to go home.
>> PROBST: All right.
It is time to vote.
Dan, you're up.
>> You're a sweet woman, but
I think this is where the
group's going.
For all I know, it could be me.
>> My vote tonight is for Kenny.
He just doesn't get a clue a lot
of the time.
So, good luck, Kenny.
>> Sorry.
I wish it wasn't you, but it is.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol, and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
>> First vote: Gillian.
Kenny.
One vote Gillian;
one vote Kenny.
Gillian.
Two votes Gillian; one vote Ken.
That's three votes Gillian;
one vote Ken.
Gillian.
That's four votes Gillian;
one vote Ken.
Second person voted out of
Survivor: Gabon: Gillian.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Gillian, the tribe has spoken.
>> Bummer.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
>> Bye, guys.
Good luck.
>> PROBST: Well, the best news
to come out of tonight's Tribal
Council is that you realize that
when you work together, you are
successful.
Now, you just need to do it a
little more often.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Randy, are you, like, the
leader of the tribe now?
>> PROBST: Fang is a tribe with
big problems.
>> No. We decided this tribe
doesn't need a leader.
Drop it.
>> I don't have to drop
nothing, man.
I can ask you something if I
want.
>> PROBST: They've lost three
challenges in a row.
Now they're in for the fight of
their lives in order to stay in
the game.
>> Let go...!
>> There's a huge part of me
that would have wished that I
could have won Survivor: Africa
because I'm still not done with
wanting to play it.
Guess it doesn't work to speak
your mind when you know you
really shouldn't.
I should have just continued
flying low under the radar, and
I didn't.
It has been an absolutely
fantastic experience, and I wish
the tribe good luck because I
think they're going to need it.