>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Brendan and Sierra
were in possession of the
hidden immunity idol at Timbira.
While their allies, Taj and
Stephen, made the discovery at
Jalapao.
>> Okay, stuff this in your
pocket.
Do something with it, hide it.
>> PROBST: Launch.
Spencer's poor defense at the
challenge cost Jalapao immunity.
So J.T. wanted to vote him out.
>> I don't have any problem
writing his name down.
>> I don't want to get rid of
anyone, but it's got to be
Spencer.
>> Everybody can kiss my ass.
>> PROBST: And Taj's
frustration at the loss caught
Joe's attention.
>> Moves like that out here will
get you voted off.
>> PROBST: But Taj was saved
when the tribe came to an
agreement.
Spencer, the tribe has spoken.
Down one member, can Jalapao
regain their momentum?
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> What's up, Big T?
>> Right.
>> Nobody wants to go.
>> They're definitely not going
to get any easier, though.
>> I know.
>> It didn't bother me at all
to see Spencer go.
Only the fact that, you know,
if there's a merge at ten,
rather than going in six-four,
we only have a shot at going in
five-five..
Within the tribe right now,
I mean, we're all united.
So if we were to lose again,
it's going to be another tough
one.
>> I'm serious, I'm tell you
straight up.
>> I definitely feel nervous
about being a target if we do
end up losing the next immunity
challenge because the boys
might stick together.
Joe is awesome in challenges,
and Stephen and J.T. are always
hanging out together.
So I feel like Taj and I are on
the chopping block.
>> You'll go to the merge.
Sydney's very nervous because
she knows that every time we
lose, she's getting potentially
closer to going home.
And Taj is a very strong
challenger for a spot in the
tribe.
But I think J.T. and Steve trust
Sydney, plus, I got a little
thing for Syd.
I mean, she's gorgeous, so
she's safe.
I mean, as far as I'm concerned,
you got a free pass.
>> I'm excited.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
(thunder rumbles)
(bird shrieking)
>> Today, we were cooking beans,
and they were finished.
But Coach likes the beans cooked
softer, so he decided to add
dirty river water.
(thunder rumbles)
>> The beans are just barely
done, and that's when they eat
them because they can't just
wait.
And actually it makes the beans
taste good.
You know, I mean, come on.
(thunder rumbles)
>> Yeah.
>> This nasty storm has been
rolling in all day.
We knew it was coming, and it's
just like, Coach, like, that's a
pretty selfish decision.
The worst part was is he put
all that stuff in there, and
then he didn't stay out there
and tend to the beans.
Instead, he just got inside the
shelter.
It's another one of those
"Coach moments."
>> It tastes funny.
>> I don't know what happened.
>> They're not good?
>> Some of these beans are
like charcoal.
>> Eventually, the rain
stopped, and the beans burned--
just stuck to the whole entire
bottom.
We lost a good amount of beans.
>> Half of our beans are burned
to the pot.
>> Gross.
>> Ew!
>> I mean, it's almost like
eating charcoal.
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> There's just a part of me
that finally just had had it.
I'm tired of feeding his needs.
>> I don't know how many times
we can clean the pot, but it's
just going to cook it more and
more each time.
>> We didn't we clean the pot
after last time?
>> I don't think that's why two
inches of buildup came onto it.
>> I'm just frustrated, as you
would have been to one of us if
we would have done it.
>> And the truth shall set you
free, Sierra.
Go and be free!
Always about the beans.
Beans, beans, beans.
Who gives a rip about these
beans?
It was really a combination
that I wanted them to cook
longer.
If it started raining, it was
just a bad combination.
No need to blame anybody.
I know, that's what's eating at
you, and you wanted to say that.
So thank you for saying that.
I will acknowledge it.
In fact, I'll take full
responsibility.
I don't care.
I screwed up the beans, my bad.
Forgive me, all of you.
Especially you, Sierra, who
seems to have the most angst
about it.
>> If you want your beans made a
different way, maybe you should
make it in a different pot.
>> I probably won't make a
separate pot for my beans.
You know, I can't believe this
is going on over such a
trivial subject.
Screw all this stuff.
It's all meaningless.
Water under the bridge,
hopefully.
It doesn't seem like it, but
hopefully it is.
>> With Coach, there's probably
five, six situations like that
where Coach has done things
where you're just like, "Come
on, that's really not for the
best of everybody.
That's for the best of just
you."
But while he does do some
irritating things, I totally
accept it because he's a
predictable player.
And predictable in this game
is-is great.
>> I know.
They're so good, though.
It's day 16, and it's getting
strange around here.
Jalapao has only five tribe
members left.
Hopefully, everyone's got a good
outlook on me.
I am a country boy, you know,
and it's hard for me to be mean
to people.
I've been honest with everyone
here at Jalapao so far, and I'm
gonna do my best to stay that
way.
Hopefully, everyone's being
honest with me as well.
(Taj laughs)
>> What do you think?
>> No, it'll work.
I just heard it cracking.
>> Well, I just think it will
solidify that I trust him
enough, you know, to tell him
the truth.
>> I just think it might make
him wary of you.
>> Mm, I see what you're saying.
>> After the last Tribal
Council, when J.T. voted for
Spencer over me, I-I just...
that's when I knew that he was
definitely in our corner.
>> Taj came and said, "I want to
tell J.T. about the idol."
Until J.T. knows, I'm basically
controlling the information flow
between Taj and J.T. and to the
extent possible, I want to
remain that bridge because if
they connect, you know, I might
become a less essential part of
the loop.
He's going to trust me less,
too.
J.T. will if we tell him about
the idol.
>> I wasn't gonna implicate
you at all.
>> Right, I'm just saying.
You haven't...
>> The real alliance for me
is my four-person alliance once
the merge happens, which is
Steve, Brendan, Sierra, and
myself.
Here I just want to make it to
the merge, and with J.T. on my
side, I'm going to be in good
shape.
>> So, you're not going to tell
him about Brendan then?
>> Oh, no, no, no.
Just about the idol.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, just about the idol.
>> No, I'm not sure at all.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Timbira getting your first look
at the new Jalapao tribe.
Spencer voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> Crazy.
>> PROBST: Guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, each tribe will have
five minutes to build a
barricade inside the other
tribe's frame.
You will then attempt to toss
ceramic pigs through the
barricade the other tribe built
in your frame.
If you drop a pig or if it
breaks, it doesn't count.
The tribe with the most pigs on
their bench at the end of ten
minutes wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: The winning tribe
will be taken to a beautiful
waterfall where you will enjoy
a relaxing afternoon barbecue.
Hamburgers, all the fixings.
In addition, the winning tribe
will choose one member from the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island.
That person will in turn choose
somebody from the winning tribe
to join them, which means
will not partake in the reward.
I know it's worth playing for.
Timbira, you have one extra
member, sitting somebody out.
Cannot sit out the same person
in back-to-back challenges.
Who's going to sit this one
out?
>> Erinn.
>> PROBST: Erinn, take a spot
on the bench.
Everybody else, we'll get
started.
Here we go, first stage.
Each tribe will have five
minutes to build a barricade in
the other tribe's frame.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, guys!
>> PROBST: The idea is to make
this as impenetrable as possible
so the other tribe can't get
their pig through.
>> Right here, just like that.
>> We need to put all these in
the front.
>> That solid?
>> No.
>> They're building X's.
>> Look what they're doing.
>> PROBST: Four minutes left.
You need to make them count.
>> PROBST: Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Stop the work.
That's it.
All right, each tribe now has
ten minutes to get as many
ceramic pigs through the
barricade built by the other
tribe as you can.
Tribe with the most pigs at the
end of ten minutes wins reward.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Can only throw one
pig at a time.
If it drops or it breaks like
that one, doesn't count.
>> Sorry.
Next.
>> Come on, guys!
>> PROBST: A lot of pigs
breaking right now.
Big learning curve here.
Brendan to Tyson.
Easily to Coach.
Coach to Sierra.
Timbira is on the board with
their first point.
There's one through.
Joe to J.T.
J.T. trying to get it to Sydney.
Low again.
Tyson and Coach have a good
rhythm going.
Timbira now with two.
>> Come on, Joe.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Nice catch by Coach.
Timbira on a roll.
Timbira now with three pigs.
>> Catch this one.
>> PROBST: J.T. to Sydney.
This time they connect.
Jalapao on the board with their
first pig.
Timbira now with four to one.
Those pigs hurt when they hit
your body.
>> Come on, Syd.
>> Nice catch by Sydney.
That's two for Jalapao.
Timbira with the fifth pig.
It's five-two.
Tyson to Coach.
Timbira with another one.
Sydney with another nice catch.
J.T. and Sydney have something
good going.
Jalapao starting to catch up.
J.T. to Sydney.
That's six-four, Timbira leads.
That's seven for Timbira.
>> Coach.
>> That's all right, Tyson.
You're the man.
>> PROBST: That's seven-five.
That's eight for Timbira.
That's six for Jalapao.
Tyson breaks another one.
>> All right, man, we got it.
>> PROBST: Timbira starting to
fall apart.
We are now eight-seven.
Joe to J.T., J.T. to Sydney.
Yes, we are tied eight-eight!
Jalapao is back in it now.
Timbira nine.
Jalapao eight.
J.T. to Sydney.
We are tied again nine-nine.
Three minutes left.
Jalapao now in the lead.
Ten-nine.
>> Come on, Joe.
>> Tyson, you're throwing them
too hard, buddy.
>> PROBST: Jalapao now with 11.
Jalapao has come from behind,
is now leading this challenge.
Jalapao with their 12th.
Timbira now with 11.
Brendan to Tyson.
Tyson snakes it through to
Coach.
Timbira now at 12.
It is neck and neck.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: One minute left.
Tyson to Coach.
Timbira with another one.
Timbira now in the lead, 13-12.
J.T. to Sydney.
That's 13, Jalapao.
We are tied 13-13.
30 seconds left.
Jalapao, you've got to make
these count.
>> I got it.
>> Let's go, guys. Let's go.
>> PROBST: Time running out.
We are still tied 13-13.
Ten seconds.
>> Catch it!
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Five, four...
>> We got it.
You betcha.
>> PROBST: three...
two, one.
That's it!
(cheering)
Timbira wins reward.
>> Give me the pig!
Let me smash it!
>> PROBST: Timbira,
congratulations.
All right, first decision.
Who from Jalapao are you going
to send to Exile Island?
>> Right now, everything with
Brendan, Sierra, and Stephen is
in place.
We have both idols.
We have the alliance intact.
So, when Timbira had to send
someone to Exile Island, all I
kept thinking was, send someone
else.
>> Joe.
>> PROBST: Joe going to Exile
Island.
Joe, grab your personal items.
Come on over.
Joe, now you have a little
power.
You get to pick somebody from
Timbira to join you on Exile,
and you will keep them from the
waterfall, burgers, all the
fixings.
>> Uh... come on, Erinn.
The decision to bring Erinn with
me to Exile was strategic
because going into a merge,
we need somebody to flip, and my
charm game is definitely part of
my strategy, and she's an
attractive woman.
>> PROBST: Who wants the map?
>> He can take it.
>> I'll take it.
>> PROBST: All right, guys.
Head out to Exile.
You'll both return in time for
the next immunity challenge.
Timbira, ready for a fun
afternoon?
>> Absolutely!
>> Like nothing else.
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff.
Head out. Enjoy it.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Thanks.
See you, guys.
>> PROBST: All right, guys.
I got nothing for you.
Jalapao, head back to camp.
>> We definitely lost a reward
today, and it sucked, but I'm
not going to feel sorry for
myself all day.
I mean, I don't really care
about the reward.
It's just a reward.
But if we lose the next immunity
challenge, we go down six-four
in numbers, so we just can't
blow it.
We need to win.
(squealing excitedly)
>> Yep.
>> High five, man.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> When we walked into the
reward, we saw, like, the
perfect all-American picnic.
I mean, watermelon, chips,
cooler of drinks.
>> Look, there's hamburgers
over there on the grill!
Oh, my God!
>> I'm going to eat enough to
puke, and then I have room for
hamburgers after that.
>> Oh, yum.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Unbelievable.
>> The first bite of the burger
was just like heaven, basically.
>> There's so much food that I
can't fit enough in my mouth.
>> Manners were out the window.
Eating as much as we could.
I mean, we were like animals.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Oh, my God, look at that
waterfall.
>> This is so amazing.
>> The water is just so crystal
clear.
It's beautiful.
>> Oh, wow.
>> A small part of me feels
guilty that Erinn is not here,
but in my opinion, she's lucky
to still be in this game.
These people right here, uh,
from the tribe, these are the
people I would have picked to be
enjoying this with.
>> Go.
(cheering)
>> All in all, a great win,
great day.
There's no bickering.
It's awesome.
It's good to feel that momentum
back, especially this late in
the game.
(laughter)
>> "You must each choose an
urn."
I insist.
Ladies first.
>> All right, he's out.
I'll see you in a while.
>> Later.
>> Joe and I came out to Exile,
picked two urns, and I got the
one with the clue in it.
It's very apparent that the idol
is not here.
It's back at camp.
And if it's back at camp,
there's more than one, so now I
just need to figure out: do I
trust Joe?
Do I not trust Joe?
Because I have no alliances out
here.
So, he could be a good ally, and
if we were aligned and had two
idols, that might not be a bad
thing for us.
>> So, who's your favorite over
there?
>> I don't know about favorites.
Can you have favorites in this?
How about you?
>> Uh, J.T.
J.T. is a good dude.
>> Yeah, he seems like it.
>> We'll be up and running here
soon.
Need any help with those clues?
>> Oh, maybe.
I'll let you know.
>> Let me know.
Maybe we can work on it together
or something.
I picked the empty urn, and I
have no clue where the idol is.
Uh, I think she knows where it's
at, so hopefully I can just get
it out of her, but we'll see how
it goes.
There's got to be one out here,
you know.
Let's go find both of them.
They're at camp?
>> I decided I was going to tell
Joe about the idol.
I'm hoping that Joe turns out to
be a trustworthy individual.
"Go to the spot where you often
get mail.
"Don't skirt the issue.
Try lifting the veil."
>> It's right there.
>> Yeah.
>> Your tree mail.
>> Easy if it's still there.
>> I'll let you know, all right?
>> Good stuff.
>> This couldn't be any better
right now.
I picked the empty urn, and now
I know where the idol is.
If Erinn and I both get the
immunity idol, that's a
humongous alliance.
It could probably rival anything
that I have back at... at camp.
(squawking)
>> When Joe comes back, he's
going to have enough clues to
find the idol in about 30
seconds.
>> Right, so we need to put
something in the tree mail ASAP.
>> I have some stuff.
I have some feathers.
I have some leather straps.
>> That will be fine.
I mean, anything that looks
authentic.
When Joe comes back from Exile
looking for the immunity idol,
he'll have all the clues, so
he'll know to look inside tree
mail, and I don't want him to
know that I already have it, so
I need to make the best-looking
little fake idol that I can come
up with.
I just went to pick up the real
idol from Stephen's pants pocket
just to know what it looks like
so I can make it look authentic
and genuine.
Hopefully, I'll be able to throw
Joe off.
(chuckling)
>> Yeah.
>> Stephen and I was going
fishing.
So, I go to grab an empty bag,
and right on top is the hidden
immunity idol.
Apparently, Taj found the idol.
And I was like, "Oh, my God."
>> I know it's right there!
When J.T. found the idol, I was
thinking what the heck do I say?
So I said, "I know," and, you
know, I don't think I had the
appropriate amount of shock on
my face.
>> Do you think she just now
found it?
>> Yeah.
>> Or that's good.
I mean, I think she was just
worried, you know, about the
next vote, so wanted to make
sure we were all on board.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, we-we got a hidden
immunity idol at camp.
>> J.T.?
>> Yeah.
>> I wanted to just talk to Taj
to tell her that J.T. found the
idol in her bag.
And she has to tell J.T. that
she has it so the three of us
are on the same page.
>> J.T.
Look.
I got you some puka berries.
>> Oh, I-I seen this a while
ago before I left.
>> Did you?
>> Yes.
>> How?
>> I walked over here...
That is beautiful.
>> Isn't it gorgeous?
>> That is beautiful.
It's a necklace, isn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> You got to hide it 'cause
it might be...
>> Where should I put it?
>> I can't believe it's the real
immunity idol.
>> I know!
Honestly, I don't want you and
Stephen to go out prematurely
for no reason.
If you need it, you can have it.
I'm serious.
>> All right.
Taj showed me the idol.
I think she felt like she could
trust me, and her sharing this
information was huge.
'Cause Taj has just made a
promise to me that any time that
I may need the hidden immunity
idol, she would give it to me.
So, that... I mean, that's big.
That's a big promise, you know.
Hopefully, she'll keep it.
>> Yeah.
>> Here.
All right, now everybody give me
theirs hands.
We're going to the merge.
>> Yeah, we're going to the end.
(gasping)
>> Taj just put herself, me, and
Stephen in a really tight
alliance.
It doesn't make me uncomfortable
that they found the idol before
Taj showed it to me.
It took her a little while to
come around, but she was honest.
And Stephen has been very honest
with me, and I feel like I can
trust Stephen all the way.
I just hope I'm not wrong.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Erinn and Joe
returning from Exile Island.
>> Hey, Erinn.
How was it?
You need a hug?
>> Welcome back.
>> (whispering): Missed you.
>> PROBST: Guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first:
take back the immunity idol.
Thank you, Sierra.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, each
tribe will use a slingshot in an
attempt to break a tile...
releasing sand from a tower.
The emptying sand will cause the
next tile to be revealed and
will release a bag of puzzle
pieces from above.
You'll retrieve the bag, move on
to the next tile.
Once you've collected all three
bags, two tribe members will use
those pieces to solve the
puzzle.
First tribe to get it right wins
immunity, safe from Tribal
Council, and guaranteed a
one-in-ten shot at winning the
million bucks.
Losers, Tribal Council, where
somebody from your tribe will be
voted out.
Timbira, you have one extra
member.
Erinn sat out the last
challenge.
Who's going to sit it out?
>> I will.
>> PROBST: Debbie, take a spot
on the bench.
Everybody else, we'll give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
J.T., the first shooter for
Jalapao.
Tyson, shooting for Timbira.
It is up to you if and when you
want to change shooters.
Survivors, ready?
Go.
>> Go, J.T.
>> PROBST: You got to break
tiles.
Oh, J.T. just misses.
Tyson just misses.
J.T.'s all around it.
Tyson connects dead center.
That second tile is being
revealed.
And there's the first bag for
Timbira.
>> Good job, good job, Tys,
good job.
All you, baby, all you.
Good shooting, Tyson.
Keep going.
>> PROBST: Tyson going to keep
shooting for Timbira.
J.T. connects, but not enough to
break the tile.
J.T. connects for Jalapao.
Sand starts pouring out.
First bag releases for Jalapao.
>> Attaboy, Jet.
>> PROBST: J.T.'s got to get it
untied.
He's got it.
>> I think I've got it.
>> Okay, keep going, bro.
>> PROBST: J.T. going to keep
shooting for Jalapao.
That sand is still pouring out
slowly revealing the second
tile.
>> Yeah, there you go.
>> PROBST: Tyson fractures the
second tile.
J.T. connects with only half a
tile to aim at.
>> Yes, Tyson.
>> PROBST: Tyson connects.
Sand pouring out of both of the
second towers.
Second bag releases for Jalapao.
>> Good job, J.T.!
>> PROBST: J.T. has the second
bag for Jalapao.
Jalapao now in the lead.
>> There we go!
There we go!
>> PROBST: Second bag releases
for Timbira.
>> Good job, good job, Tys,
good job.
>> Close.
>> PROBST: J.T. didn't
completely break those first two
tiles, so not enough sand is
leaking out, which means J.T.'s
target on that third tile will
not get any larger than it is
right now.
It has been J.T. and Tyson all
the way.
Nobody else has fired a shot.
J.T. nicking at that tile.
>> Almost.
>> So close, buddy.
You got it, Jet.
>> Come on.
>> You got it, man.
You got it. Come on.
One more.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Tyson connects.
>> PROBST: With a big break.
Third bag releases for Timbira.
J.T.'s got to pick it up, now.
>> Jet, you want to keep going?
>> Yeah, I think I got it, Joe.
>> I'll come over and do it if
you want.
>> PROBST: Timbira has their
third and final bag.
Two people now working on the
puzzle.
Time to pick up the pace now.
Firing as fast as he can.
Trying to get Jalapao back in
this.
Brendan and Erinn take their
time with a big lead on the
puzzle.
>> Like that.
>> Oh, yeah, okay.
>> Just keep trying all the
different spots.
>> PROBST: J.T. continues to
surround the tile with hits.
>> Oh!
Man!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: J.T. connects.
Now the sand starts to pour out.
That'll do it.
>> Yes!
>> Yes, J.T.!
>> PROBST: Jalapao's third bag
is released.
J.T. has it.
Start working on the puzzle,
Jalapao.
>> Come on, Joe.
>> PROBST: Steven and Joe
working on the puzzle for
Jalapao.
Timbira has had a big head
start, tough puzzle, still time.
Jalapao could be right back in
this.
>> Nope.
No, it doesn't fit.
>> Hold on, one more.
>> That fits, there.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Brendan and Erinn
slowly figuring out the puzzle.
>> I got one.
>> PROBST: Joe with the first
piece for Jalapao.
Timbira thinks they have another
piece.
>> Hustle, hustle, guys.
>> There's two.
>> PROBST: Jalapao starting to
pick it up now.
>> Is that it?
>> Yep, yep, yep.
Oh, look at that. Look at that.
>> Fits.
>> No, keep trying.
>> That's it, okay.
>> There it is right here.
Right here.
>> Ooh.
>> No, that-that's it right
there, and spin it.
Got it.
>> PROBST: Timbira thinks they
have it.
And they do.
Timbira wins immunity!
(cheering)
>> Oh, J.T., it's okay.
>> Don't beat yourself up.
>> PROBST: Timbira,
congratulations.
Once again immunity is yours.
>> Thank you.
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: What's it feel like
right now, Coach, knowing no
chance I'm going home tonight?
>> It's incredible.
And I really think that this was
so pivotal, this win, because it
really shifts control of the
game.
>> PROBST: Timbira, grab your
stuff.
Head back to camp.
Enjoy the night off.
Jalapao, I got nothing for you
except a date with me once again
at Tribal Council, where one of
you will be going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> It's not a good thing to go
to Tribal Council.
I've been told by Joe I am safer
than Taj, but you know, no one's
safe at this point.
And it really just sucks.
♪ ♪
>> Damn!
I'm sorry, guys.
>> Man, I want to say nobody
blames you at all.
>> No, not at all.
>> It's hard not to.
>> Every challenge you're at,
you give your all, and like this
time it didn't work out as well.
>> Are you all right, man?
>> Your leg looks bad.
It's red all the way down from
the knee to the ankle.
>> Pretty painful.
This should be good, like,
tomorrow.
>> Oh, man, that place sucks.
What do you think?
>> No way?
You didn't?
>> I let her go first.
I go, "I insist."
>> She didn't show it to you?
>> I tried to juice her for
info.
>> Nothing?
>> Nada.
>> Wow, that's weird.
>> It was a long two days, man.
>> I need some water.
(laughing)
>> At Exile, Erinn gave me a
scroll with five clues on it,
and it was really easy.
I mean, I walked up and got the
idol in literally ten seconds.
This is the hidden immunity
idol.
"Don't skirt the issue.
Try lifting the veil.
Here it is."
I was stoked.
Just pure relief.
Now I feel like I got a great
shot at extra time in this game.
>> Tonight, we are all voting
for Taj.
Joe made sure we were all on the
same page, and that's that.
I think Taj knows something's
up, but she's not someone who's
trying to stab people behind
their backs or trying to talk
crap right before we have Tribal
Council.
She's not that kind of person.
>> I don't believe I have
anything to worry about tonight
at Tribal Council.
I think I have Stephen and
J.T.'s trust completely, and
plus I have the idol.
>> Yeah, it's perfect.
>> I think Sydney believes
everything is going to work in
her favor because Joe is going
to protect her, but I'm pretty
confident tonight I'm not going.
(laughs)
>> Yeah.
>> Taj, myself, and Stephen have
a tight alliance right now, and
Taj has got the hidden immunity
idol that I could use.
You know, that's just like my
idol, and there's no way I could
vote my hidden immunity idol out
of this game right now.
He's gonna want to know why it's
got to be Sydney and not Taj.
>> Whoo!
Oh, dude.
>> It feels good, don't it?
>> Yeah, man.
>> We should at least talk about
it.
>> I go to the water to talk
with J.T. and Steve, and they
got this crazy look in their eye
about keeping Taj.
They started talking out all
these plans that could happen,
but I kind of envisioned Taj
being the odd man out and going
home should we lose.
I need to try to honor that.
The three of us were not in any
agreement on who to vote for
tonight, and if J.T. and Steve--
they don't really give me
consideration, then I might hand
over the idol to Sydney and make
a point.
(thunder rumbles)
(Stephen sighs)
>> We don't want that.
>> Uh-uh, and if we get rid of
her, the idol's gone, too.
>> Well, that's not true.
>> She gave it to you, didn't
she?
You have the idol.
She told you to put it in your
pocket and keep it.
>> That means it's technically
mine.
>> It's your idol right now.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, that guarantees you
and I have the idol.
Oh, man, this is tough.
I do believe Taj is comfortable
right now because she has a very
strong alliance with Stephen and
myself, but the idol is in
Stephen and my possession
already, so I could vote Taj out
right now, and we'll still have
the idol.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
I'm probably gonna decide when I
get there.
This is terrible.
I'm going to hell.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: J.T., give me the
state of affairs of this game
right now.
Where does it sit?
>> Jeff, it ain't sitting real
good for Jalapao right now.
You know, we're down two members
after tonight, and if there's a
merge, we're down and out.
>> PROBST: Stephen, how much
time is spent talking about a
possible merge?
>> It's looming real large for
us, and especially now that
we're about to be down to four
tribe members, you know, we're
all a little bit intimidated of
what might happen.
>> PROBST: Joe, if you do merge,
just based on numbers, you're in
trouble.
So how much of tonight's vote is
going to be made based on a
possible merge?
>> I would say the vote tonight
is based on trust.
To go into a merge, I want
somebody who I know I can share
information with, they'll share
information with me, and it
won't leave outside that.
>> PROBST: Taj, is this a point
in the game where being on Exile
so many days can work against
you?
You've spent so much time with
people from the other tribe, you
could have the idol.
You have a lot of potential
weapons.
>> Definitely, but I don't think
it's a matter that they don't
trust me.
It's just the situations that
I've been in are distrustful.
>> PROBST: So if you guys were
to merge, how are you going to
help these other four people get
further in the game?
>> Well, I think that I will be
able to create relationships on
the other side with Timbira.
I've been on Exile with Sierra
and Brendan, so I think I could
probably talk them into maybe
flipping over on our side.
I think I'd be valuable in that
way.
>> PROBST: J.T., the flip side
of what Taj is talking about is
she's made relationships.
You haven't.
>> Exactly.
I worry about that, too, Jeff,
you know.
She could always fall in with
them and start another alliance,
and we'd still be sitting ducks.
>> PROBST: Sydney, how about
you?
What do you bring that could
help the rest of Jalapao if you
merge?
>> Well, I mean, it's not like I
spent Exile time with a bunch of
people from the other tribe, so
I definitely bring loyalty to
these people.
>> PROBST: So you are the flip
of Taj.
Taj is saying, "I have
relationships.
I will utilize them."
You're saying, "I don't have any
relationships.
I'm loyal to the tribe I was
born into."
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Joe, one of the
advantages Timbira has with the
numbers is they have options.
Jalapao doesn't have any
options.
If you guys don't stick
together, you're in trouble.
>> That's why I feel it's so
important to go into the merge
knowing that you at least have
four, and you can't have any
doubt that they're going to, you
know, do anything drastic and
leave you.
>> PROBST: So dead set, know
what you're doing tonight on the
vote?
>> Yeah, I'm ready to put pencil
to paper.
>> PROBST: J.T., any questions
in your mind as we get ready to
vote?
>> All afternoon, Jeff, and it's
still going through my mind
right now.
Here I am: I blew the challenge
today, and I got to make a
decision to send someone home.
It's a terrible situation for me
to be in right now.
>> PROBST: Well, the time has
come to make that decision.
It is time to vote.
Joe, you're up.
>> This is not an easy decision.
Good luck.
>> (whispering): Love you, girl.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol, and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sydney.
Taj.
One vote Sydney;
one vote Taj.
Taj.
Two votes Taj;
one vote Sydney.
Sydney.
We're tied.
Two votes Sydney;
two votes Taj;
one vote left.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins: Sydney.
>> Ha.
>> PROBST: You need to bring me
your torch.
Sydney, the tribe has spoken.
Well, there was a lot of
discussion tonight about a
possible merge.
If indeed you guys merge down
two members, you've got your
work cut out for you.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
(screaming)
>> Congratulations, tribe.
You have merged.
(cheering)
>> If the old Timbira were to
stay together, we can eliminate
them one by one by one.
>> We're going into this four on
six.
That's not good odds.
We're sitting ducks.
>> I'm pissed I was voted off.
Jalapao is in trouble if there's
a merge.
They are down the numbers, and I
don't really see anyone from
Timbira switching over, but Taj
might try to do something.
It was a great experience, and
being able to look back on it
and say that I got to do that is
a blessing in itself, so I feel
very lucky.