>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> It's a merge!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: The tribes merge.
>> To the merge, hear, hear!
>> PROBST: And they name
themselves "Forza."
The old Jalapao came in with
only four members to Timbira's
six.
>> We're in control, baby.
>> PROBST: And J.T. became the
target.
>> Right now, J.T. needs to go.
>> PROBST: But some former
Timbira members made new
friends.
And new plans.
>> In my alliance now, Stephen
and J.T. have replaced Brendan
and Sierra.
>> PROBST: Feeling safe, Brendan
ignored his Exile alliance...
leaving Taj open to new ideas.
But everyone's plans were cut
short when Joe was evacuated.
Joe's been battling a pretty
decent infection.
Medical did a thorough
assessment.
He can't continue.
>> What?!
>> PROBST: So, no Tribal
Council.
>> Brendan lives to see
another day.
Now, I don't know what's going
to happen.
>> PROBST: Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> That sucks.
Joe left camp today, and it was
just kind of this funk that was
permeating the camp.
And we're sitting around there,
looking at the fire.
Nobody was saying anything.
And I just wanted to share a
piece of my life with them.
I wanted to show them that no
matter how bad it gets in your
life, there's always something
that's going to make it much
worse.
>> I want to hear this story.
>> So, I shared with the tribe
one of the stories about the
time that I got caught in the
Amazon and thought I was going
to get killed.
Now, they were probably, you
know, four, four and a half
feet tall.
I paddled so hard that my hands
started bleeding.
>> You don't want to say,
"Coach, hey, let's have a
reality check here.
But no one said a word.
It was silent when he finished
and everybody was kind of going
around looking at each other,
like, "Whoa!"
>> How much does it cost to get
a military copter to drop you
in?
>> That would be free.
>> How?
>> Honestly, like, you know,
Coach is either the new coming
of Jacques Cousteau, or he's,
you know, basically the biggest
fraud that is in this game.
>> They were just, like,
ecstatic that I wanted to come
down there.
>> I don't believe this guy
anymore.
And if I don't believe his
stories, how I can believe what
he's saying to my face?
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
(bird calling)
>> What's he doing?
>> Warrior poses.
>> He likes to do that in the
morning.
>> He's kind of like a snake.
>> Oh, yeah, he's like a snake,
ready to strike.
>> Don't bother him and he
won't bother you.
>> Brendan is targeting me for
the next Tribal Council.
But I am involved in a power
alliance right now, uh, the
alliance is Coach, myself,
Tyson, Stephen, and Debbie,
so Brendan is going home.
>> Hi, guys.
>> I was watching you.
>> I'm having a great day so
far.
>> What's it from?
Like, where is that...?
>> Yeah, it's called chong ran.
And it's, uh, ancient Tibetan.
If you do a Google search on
it, you won't find it.
It's only passed down verbally.
You have to go there to the
monastery to study it.
>> Wow.
>> Bow and arrow pose?
>> I feel like I'm in control
of this game.
I have the power alliance,
commanding my officers, running
the show, like I was born to do.
You know, if you look at it, to
defeat an army, you have to cut
off the head of the dragon,
which is why I nicknamed
Brendan "the dragon."
Hence, my name, the
"Dragonslayer."
Where does Sierra fit into all
this?
With the comments that she made
today, Sierra is the bowel
movements that come out of the
dragon.
After Brendan, Sierra's got to
go.
>> Worried about Joe?
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm sure he's
doing fine.
I hate having him leave the
game.
>> I know.
Well, you guys were such good
friends, too.
>> I know.
>> Like, I was so happy to have
met him.
It was so nice to know that
like, Joe was going to be here,
and I was going to have, you
know, somebody that I knew I
could go to with stuff.
And then for that to not happen,
I was so bummed.
And I just like him, you know,
like, he's a cool guy.
>> He's a cool guy.
He's a real cool guy.
Stephen as well.
Stephen's an awesome guy.
>> Yeah, I really like him.
Well, I like all you guys.
I'm like, "How do I like your
tribe more than I like my own?"
>> Are you aligned with anyone
here now?
>> Um, aligned, not so much.
I've kind of stayed pretty
neutral, but, you know,
regardless of who I'm talking
to or whatever, the only
alliance I had in this game was
Joe, so...
When you break it down, you've
got my original tribe, where we
knew I was the first one out.
Then I have these new kids who
are down in numbers and really
need a fourth.
But no matter how the dice
rolls, I've got some room to
play around.
It's really nice.
>> Things are in our favor
right now.
>> Yeah, because like I said,
I like you guys more than I like
my own tribe.
>> Erinn's vote would be huge,
you know, because I lost Joe.
He was a huge, solid vote.
But now, Taj, myself, Stephen,
and Erinn could easily turn the
game around.
So, it's good to know if I need
her, I can call on her.
I know things are different
from the time I got here.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will be divided
into teams of three.
Each team will have one row of
eight color-coded ceramic tiles.
On my go, one member from each
team will toss a metal ball,
attempting to knock out one of
the tiles of the other two
teams.
When you're out of tiles,
you're out of the challenge.
Last team left standing wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: The winning threesome
will be taken on an afternoon
of whitewater river rafting down
the Rio Novo.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: This is world-class
river rafting, an experience
you will not soon forget.
After the rafting trip, you
will have a nice picnic,
sandwiches, chicken wings,
brownies.
>> Brownies!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning threesome will choose
one member of either of the two
losing teams to go to Exile
Island alone.
A lot at stake.
You guys ready to get to it?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for teams
and we'll get started.
All right, we have our teams:
Debbie, Brendan, J.T.
Tyson, Taj, Coach.
Stephen, Sierra, and Erinn.
Here we go.
First shooters, head up.
Your goal is to break the tile
of one of the other teams, not
your own.
>> Stephen!
Stephen, man, what are you
doing?!
>> PROBST: Stephen and Coach
going for black.
Debbie going for red.
Here we go: three, two, one.
Toss.
Debbie knocks out a red tile.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Stephen and Coach
both knock out a black tile.
Black team loses two tiles in
that round.
>> Come on. Let's go.
>> Easy, Coach.
>> Next group.
Sierra's going to go red; Tyson
going after black.
>> Why is everybody after the
black team?
>> Your team is a little
stacked, I think.
>> We're throwing underhand
breaking tiles.
None of us have ever done this
in our lives.
>> I have.
>> Coach likes to have the
attention.
I mean, all the great stuff
he's done.
Sounds almost too good to be
true.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Three, two, one, toss.
Brendan breaks a white tile.
Sierra takes out a red tile
Tyson gets nothing.
Black is down two tiles.
Red is down two tiles.
White is down one tile.
The more tiles you have, the
better off you are.
Brendan breaks a white tile.
J.T. with a long toss.
Sierra's on fire!
Connects, knocking out a
white tile.
Tyson wipes out a white tile.
>> Yeah!
My first one today!
>> PROBST: With that round, red
is now down to one tile left.
Black team, white team, each
have two tiles left.
We are getting down to it.
Debbie going for white; Stephen
and Coach going for black.
Three, two, one, toss.
Debbie tosses and misses.
Stephen misses.
Coach annihilates a black
tile.
Black team now down with one
tile left.
The red team has one tile left,
and the white team has two
tiles left.
>> Finish the red off.
And I'll miss, Erinn.
>> Okay.
>> Oh, oh, you want to send her
to red?!
Oh, okay.
>> All right, well, I'll get
right (indistinct)
>> Taj, come over there with
white.
Go back to white with J.T.
>> PROBST: Erinn is trying to
take out the last tile for the
red team.
>> Erinn, I'm going to whip
your tail.
>> PROBST: J.T. and Taj
attempting to take out the
last two tiles for the
white team.
Three, two, one, toss.
Erinn knocks out the last
remaining red tile.
The red team is now out of this
challenge.
Sierra could put the black team
out of this and win it for the
white team with one toss.
Three, two, one, toss.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Sierra short.
Brendan takes out another white
tile.
Black team, white team each
have one tile left.
This could do it.
Erinn for the white team,
J.T. for the black team.
Three, two, one.
Toss.
Erinn goes deep, just too far.
J.T. just too short.
>> Oh, I thought that was it,
man.
Deb, come on.
>> PROBST: Debbie and Stephen,
each looking to take out the
last tile of the other team.
Three, two, one, toss.
Debbie, no chance.
Stephen, no chance.
Sierra and Brendan.
Brendan looking to win it for
the black team.
Three, two, one.
Toss.
Oh!
>> PROBST: Sierra short.
Brendan clips it, but not
enough.
That white tile is clipped,
but it is still standing.
>> Oh, man!
>> PROBST: It still counts.
J.T. going to try to put the
finishing touches on that white
tile.
Erinn would like to win it for
the white team.
Three, two, one, toss.
>> PROBST: Erinn with a good
toss.
>> Nope, it's not down.
>> PROBST: Erinn knocks the
black tile, but it doesn't fall.
It cannot get any closer than
this.
Both tiles have been broken.
Neither one of them has fallen
through.
Stephen, you may not even have
to hit that tile.
You might just hit the wood.
The vibration may knock it in.
>> Stephen, don't do nothing
crazy now.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
toss.
>> Oh, no!
>> PROBST: Debbie too far,
Stephen too short.
Big reward on the line:
whitewater river rafting, nice
picnic, brownies, chicken
wings, sandwiches.
>> Oh, my God, this is a
nailbiter.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Three, two, one, toss.
Sierra short.
Brendan knocks out the final
white tile.
Black team wins reward.
Black team, come on over.
J.T., Debbie, Brendan, nice job.
Before we send you on a nice
reward, you have a big decision
to make.
Figure out which person you are
sending to Exile Island.
They are going alone.
They will not be choosing
anybody to go with them.
>> Stephen.
>> PROBST: Stephen, grab your
stuff.
>> Be the wizard, Stephen.
Be the wizard.
>> PROBST: A map, even though
you've been there before.
Head back out the way you came.
>> Sorry, Stephen.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
No, it's my pleasure.
>> PROBST: Stephen will return
in time for the next immunity
challenge.
All right, J.T., Brendan,
Debbie, nice reward.
Whitewater river rafting,
nice afternoon picnic.
It will be a nice little break.
You will head back to camp and
go on your reward tomorrow.
Got it.
>> PROBST: All right, guys,
sadly, I got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff and head back
to camp.
>> Thanks, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Coach, you can, uh,
leave that behind.
>> I'm sorry.
I'm so pissed off right now.
>> I wanted to get on that river
in some type of raft or kayak
since I got here.
>> I mean, I expect Brendan
trying to scheme.
I'm not really that worried,
Brendan being gone with J.T.
and Debbie.
Those are two of the strongest
allies.
So, it actually worked out well.
I just hope the extra food
Brendan gets isn't going to
hurt our chances for winning
immunity.
>> Clue six: "A big wooden head
is what you have here.
Look in the gap that you'll
find in the rear."
No surprise here.
Great.
This is my first Exile out here
alone.
It's the first of anybody's
Exiles out here alone, and I got
the new clue to the same idols
that we know about.
So, I know there's no new idol
in the game.
I'm definitely concerned about
being on Exile.
I haven't made fire yet at camp.
I tried a few times and I
failed, and I was so
embarrassed I hadn't tried
again.
So, I knew that by forcing
myself to come out here, either
I would make fire, make food,
or I would die.
It looked like I might die.
I was trying for about an hour
or two to make fire, just
smacking that flint over and
over again with a machete.
And nothing.
How about that!
Damn, I can build a fire!
Finally, as darkness was
starting to close around me,
I got a spark; it caught; and
the whole thing took.
It was like giving birth to my
first child.
I felt so proud of that little
fire that I just wanted to stay
out here and tend to it for the
rest of my life.
So, even though I missed out on
that good lunch and a fun,
relaxing, water rafting trip,
being out here and making it
is like winning my own reward.
>> Brendan, myself, and Debbie
went to the reward, and we had
a blast.
I've actually never been able
to go whitewater rafting and
that's something I've always
wanted to do forever.
I felt just like a little kid.
>> A-ha!
>> Yeah!
>> Great job!
>> The reward was so much fun.
The pure joy that was on J.T.'s
face to see how much he just
soaks it up and appreciates it.
What a great soul.
So sincere, so real.
Like, all qualities that you
want in people that surround
you or at least I do.
>> Forza!
>> After we did, like, the best
rafting ever, we came along
this huge sandbar and I knew it
was our picnic.
>> This is amazing!
I've died and gone to heaven.
Chips!
There's chips!
Oh, my God!
Look at those brownies!
Whoo!
Oh, my God.
This is the best food in the
world.
>> Oh, my God!
I had a really good day.
I mean, it was a lot better
than I had pictured.
I figured Brendan and I being
together would kind of be a
dull trip, but there wasn't a
dull moment at all.
>> No?
>> About what?
>> Just about how to, you know.
>> Keep me in the game a little
longer.
>> Have some fun.
>> If there's an opportunity,
I damn sure will do what I can
do, whatever I can.
>> All right, yeah.
I always kind of define winning
in a lot of my life of saying
like, I'm going to be #1.
If I take J.T. in the finals
with me, he's going to beat me.
I know it's crazy, but for me,
winning in this game is about
getting to an outcome at the
end of the game which is going
to satisfy me.
If he wins it, that's like me
winning this game.
How do I get him to the finals?
I don't know.
That's the next step I need to
wrap my head around.
Let's have some fun.
>> I'm definitely up for it,
man.
>> I stayed up all night.
I sat in that shelter and did
not sleep at all, just running
through all the different
scenarios about how do I get
J.T. to the finals.
And at a certain point, all the
pieces, like, just fell and you
could see the puzzle and how it
needs to be put together.
>> Here's how we're gonna do
it.
Um, I don't think we should send
J.T. home.
We had the awesome time.
He's such a good dude.
Debbie had such a good time
with him.
>> He is.
He's one of the most amazing
people I have ever met in my
life.
>> I think what we should do is
you, me, Taj, Stephen, J.T.,
take out Tyson, Coach, and
Erinn.
Start taking them out.
>> This morning, Brendan is
like, "All right, here's what's
going on.
I really like J.T.
I think J.T. deserves to be
here," and I feel the same way.
Like, I really respect J.T.
So, we're going to try to get
Coach and Tyson.
>> Okay, so, I know how to do
it.
>> Change it?
How?
>> You, me, Stephen, J.T.,
and Sierra...
>> Okay.
Okay, okay.
>> And, Taj?
>> Yes?
>> We haven't talked...
>> I know, we haven't had a
chance to.
>> That's got to make you
uncomfortable, but you, like,
you gotta trust me.
>> I can't describe Timbira.
I really want to know what that
word stands for because it
could mean "confused."
Coach and Tyson want to
blindside Brendan, and, um,
Brendan is trying it vote out
Tyson or Coach.
We haven't even had to really
put any plans into action yet
because they're so busy trying
to get out their own tribe
members right now.
We're like, "Okay, do what you
gotta do and we'll come in
later."
>> Sierra knows the plan.
Yesterday, on the river trip,
I talked to J.T. and I was like
"J.T., I think I can save you."
He's such a good dude.
>> I know, he is.
I love him to death, and I
don't want him to go.
>> No, I agree. I agree.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Stephen,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Welcome back, buddy.
>> PROBST: You were out there
for a while on Exile this time.
>> It was a couple of days
alone, yeah, but actually, not
that bad.
The weather was pretty good.
I had big fires both nights.
I didn't get much sleep, but it
was, you know, it was all right.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to
get to today's challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Tyson, hand back the necklace.
>> It's too gaudy for me anyway.
>> PROBST: Does that mean you
don't want it again?
>> Oh, I'll probably wear it
again.
>> PROBST: All right.
For today's challenge, you will
each be attached to a long rope
that is threaded through a
series of obstacles.
You'll climb over, crawl under,
maneuver around these obstacles
as you race to the finish.
First three to finish move on
to the final round, where, once
again, you will be attached to
one long rope, only this time,
the obstacle is three levels
high.
It will seriously complicate
things.
First person to finish wins
immunity, guaranteed a
one-in-eight shot
at winning this game.
Losers, Tribal Council, where
somebody will be going home.
We'll draw for spots and get
started.
Here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
There is a learning curve to
this challenge.
Things that will help make
getting around this rope a
little easier, but there are no
shortcuts.
J.T. off to a quick start.
Tyson off to a quick start.
Debbie, J.T., Tyson, all doing
very well.
Coach flying through the course.
Brendan right in there.
Sierra hanging in there.
Taj struggling, in dead last.
Stephen not doing a lot better.
Erinn right in there.
It's Tyson and J.T. battling
it out right now.
Sierra's now through.
It's Tyson, J.T., and Sierra.
Brendan's through.
Coach frustrated, stuck.
Nothing prepared him for the
rope-a-dope.
Tyson and J.T., neck and neck.
Erinn now moving on to the next
obstacle.
Tyson has finished the second
Tyson now on the last obstacle,
J.T. right behind him.
Tyson and J.T. in very good
shape.
Three people are moving on to
the final.
The other six will have no shot
at immunity.
J.T. throwing himself over this
challenge.
Brendan now on to the last
obstacle.
It is Tyson, J.T., and Brendan.
Sierra now is in it.
Four people fighting for three
spots.
Taj and Stephen still back on
the first obstacle.
J.T. very close.
Tyson very close.
It's going to come down to
Brendan and Sierra for that
final spot.
Brendan with a bit of a lead
over Sierra.
J.T. is across first.
J.T. moving on to the final.
Tyson is across.
Tyson moving on to the final.
Brendan and Sierra battling for
one final spot.
Brendan losing his shoes.
Brendan moves on to the final!
Tyson, J.T., and Brendan, moving
on to the final.
Here we go, for immunity.
Tyson, J.T., Brendan.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First round was very close.
Only one will win immunity.
A lot of bodies being launched.
Tyson off to an early lead.
J.T. is right behind him.
Cannot fall behind in this
challenge.
Tyson and J.T. very close.
Brendan right in there.
Brendan now in the lead.
>> Keep going, J.T.!
>> PROBST: Brendan still with a
lead over J.T. and Tyson.
Tyson making up some ground now.
Getting down to it.
It is Brendan and Tyson.
J.T. has fallen out of it.
On the last part of this course,
Tyson now with the lead.
>> Tyson!
>> PROBST: Tyson flying through
this.
Tyson wins immunity!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Tyson saved the day ensuring
that Brendan would go home
tonight.
In case he plays the immunity
idol, we're gonna split the
votes, four for Brendan,
three for Sierra.
Brendan is the dragon.
I'm the dragonslayer.
This is gonna be the biggest
power move to date of this game,
no question about it.
>> PROBST: Tyson, come on over.
>> Tyson!
>> PROBST: As he predicted, for
the second time, Tyson has
immunity once again.
Tyson's safe at Tribal Council.
Not the same for the rest of
you.
One of you going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> Tyson won the immunity.
We can't vote Tyson.
So, I decided on Coach.
It will be nice to have him out
of here, I think.
>> Congratulations.
>> Thanks, dude.
You were awesome.
>> Seriously, it was a delight
watching you.
It was like something out of...
>> Dude, you need a hug, man.
>> You need a hug.
>> You got your fire started.
>> I got my fire started.
>> Oh, you were so worried.
>> Unfortunately I spent like an
hour just chopping at that flint
and I made it and it was like,
it was actually one of the best
moments of my life.
>> Oh!
>> For me, it was a big step.
>> I'm very proud of you.
>> We missed your poetry
yesterday.
I feel like I have no skills at
all.
>> You know what I did?
>> I started this plan to
eliminate Brendan days ago,
but due to default, we didn't
even go to Tribal.
I've already got it set up so
four votes go to Brendan,
three votes go to Sierra.
If Brendan gets wind of it and
uses his idol, Sierra is gone.
Brendan's gone in three days
from that.
I'd like to see him go first
because I'd like three days of
just bossing her around and
telling her to shut up.
Probably won't win me her vote
from the jury, but it would
probably win me everybody else's
vote, so... so it would be a
win-win for me.
>> What is it?
>> Water.
>> All right, can we just sit
down real quick?
>> Yeah.
>> The Exile alliance
hibernated for a while.
Uh, it's finally going to rear
its ugly head.
>> I talked to Taj this morning.
I think we go after Coach.
We get us four and Taj, I had
an extensive conversation with
Taj this morning about it.
>> Okay.
>> You guys cool?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Myself, Sierra, Taj, Stephen,
and now J.T. are all voting
Coach.
I think that this will be one
of the biggest blindsides
so far in the game.
Um, so, I guess I'm happy to be
a part of on the good side.
>> I thought you might.
Wow, that changes everything.
>> He said he wants me in the
finals.
>> Why would he want that?
>> He likes me a lot.
>> But that's crazy.
>> I know.
>> It would be a really strong
play.
We might have to seriously
think about it.
>> You know what, he's crazy.
He is somewhat crazy.
I think that story about him
being captured on the Amazon,
that's just hard to believe.
>> That is pretty hard to
believe.
>> I mean, (indistinct) I mean,
I wouldn't reckon with them son
of a bitches, don't you think?
I would have come back with a
damn .30-.30 Winchester.
Something, you know what I mean?
>> I would definitely say we're
in control of this game now.
>> It's a big difference, you
know?
Jalapao came into the merge
down in numbers, but before the
first Tribal Council we come to,
I'm the deciding factor.
It's huge.
I can go with Brendan right now
and get rid of Coach or I can
go with Coach and Tyson and get
rid of Brendan.
It's completely in my court.
>> Clean pots and water.
>> Clean pots and water?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm looking forward to
Tribal.
The old Timbira is going to go
after J.T., but I'm going to
take out Coach.
>> Sierra's got that pot...
>> She does?
>> I don't like misleading
people, but I feel like this is
the one time in life that you're
actually allowed to do it and
you get a get-out-of-jail-free
pass.
>> I'm down with that.
>> Okay.
>> Tyson.
>> J.T.?
>> Yeah.
>> Just pass it around.
>> Okay.
>> Pass it around, make sure
everybody knows.
Everybody already pretty much
knows.
>> Sierra, you good?
>> Yeah.
Done.
>> Done and done?
Okay.
Yeah, okay, cool.
>> Brendan suspects nothing.
In fact, Brendan still thinks
we're going to vote J.T. off.
But in reality, we're cutting
the head off the dragon and
sending Brendan home, and I
feel very happy about that.
You know, leaders are born.
I'm not saying Brendan is not a
naturally born leader, but when
it comes head-to-head, we'll
see tonight who really was the
Chosen One.
It's going to be Coach way.
So, that's very fulfilling.
>> PROBST: So, you guys have
spent a little bit of time
together as one tribe.
Erinn, I'm guessing certain
roles are emerging.
Who's the person that keeps the
tribe laughing?
>> Tyson.
He just always has some sort of
offhanded, witty comment to
make.
He's kind of the class clown.
>> PROBST: J.T., who tells the
best campfire stories?
>> Uh, Coach probably tells the
best campfire stories, no doubt.
>> PROBST: Taj, what's the best
story Coach has told?
>> Well, I love the Amazon story
because he told us about how he
was captured by this tribe and
he was beaten and he escapes and
he's, like, paddling for two
days down the Amazon River to
get away.
It's so unbelievable.
It was incredible.
>> PROBST: Coach, this really
happened or this is a movie
version of what you want to
have happened?
>> I tried to actually tone it
down because if I tell them,
you know, that the tribe was,
you know, looking at my ass,
talking about eating my ass,
so, actually, you know, when I
tell these stories, I usually
try to give like the "PG-13"
version of it.
>> PROBST: Coach, does it bother
you that some people might
question these stories?
>> What I've been through in my
life, it's pretty fantastic.
I got, you know, scars all over
my body that I can point to,
of the, you know, five, six,
seven, eight, life or
death situations I've been
through.
PROBST: Five, six, seven, or
eight life-or-death situations?
>> Probably more than that, I
mean, if you want me to recount
them I will.
I've been through a hurricane.
I've been attacked by a
shark, had a run-in with a
crocodile, got captured by the
Indian tribe; I mean, there were
some very defining moments
in my life where I thought these
were the last three or four
seconds.
So, it doesn't bother me
that people wanna question that.
They cannot question my
integrity and my honesty.
That's how I'm playing this
game.
That's how I play my life.
>> PROBST: From the beginning,
Coach, you've talked about the
numbers, sticking together,
having a strong group.
Still feel confident about that?
>> I do feel confident about
tonight's vote.
>> PROBST: Tyson, how big is
trust in tonight's vote?
>> If one of the Jalapao
members goes home, then I
think that Timbiras stayed
loyal, and if for some reason a
Timbira tribe member does go
home, I think everybody will
seriously rethink, uh, their
strategies.
>> PROBST: Stephen, how does
that sit with you?
What can you do, if anything,
to change your fate?
>> You know, in my case, I'm
just hoping I have enough time
to get to know more people.
I'm really glad that J.T. is
over there with a much larger
target on his back than I
have on mine.
>> PROBST: Taj, do you think
that's true?
The people that are the most
physically threatening at
challenges are now gonna be
the biggest targets?
>> Yeah, I definitely think so.
I mean, J.T. is fast.
He's a lovable person.
He's like a triple threat
because you just can't find
anything wrong with him.
>> PROBST: Coach, you agree
with that?
If you're a physical threat in
this game, it's time for you to
go?
>> The seven layers of heaven
with the Vikings were
determined on how they were
defeated in battle.
I want to surround myself with
warriors.
>> PROBST: So, Brendan...
>> Even if that means that they
defeat me, I think that that's
the honorable way to play this
game.
>> PROBST: Brendan, biggest
physical threats going to be the
first to go?
>> It's natural to kind of want
to go after the strong, but just
because you're strong doesn't
mean you go deep in this game.
>> PROBST: Tyson, has there been
much talk about the idol and
that it's hidden, meaning
somebody might have it and
nobody knows?
>> I just assumed that everybody
that's been to Exile could
possibly have the idol.
And if I figure out who has it
then great; if not, everybody
who's been there has it.
>> PROBST: Taj, how does that
make you feel?
You've been to Exile.
>> I don't have it.
>> PROBST: Erinn, do you have
it?
>> I don't have it.
>> PROBST: Stephen, do you have
it?
>> No.
>> Brendan, do you have it?
>> I have it.
>> PROBST: Brendan has it.
All right, at least we've
cleared that up.
You guys ready to get to the
vote?
Tyson has the individual
immunity idol.
I take it you're keeping it for
yourself?
All right, cannot vote for
Tyson.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
J.T., you're up.
>> The ancient samurai used to
say that if you wanted to win
the war, you had to cut off the
head of the dragon.
You, my friend, are the dragon,
and I am the dragonslayer.
>> This is my wizard lightning
shooting you back home.
Ga-bow!
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Coach.
Coach.
Two votes Coach.
Brendan.
Two votes Coach;
one vote Brendan.
Brendan.
Two votes coach;
two votes Brendan.
Brendan.
That's three votes Brendan;
two votes Coach.
Sierra.
That's three votes Brendan;
two votes Coach;
one vote Sierra.
Sierra.
Three votes Brendan;
two votes Coach;
two votes Sierra.
We're tied.
Three votes Sierra;
three votes Brendan;
two votes Coach.
One vote left.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins, and the
first member of our jury:
Brendan.
You need to bring me your torch.
Brendan, the tribe has spoken.
>> Good luck, fellas.
>> PROBST: Well, judging by the
amount of smiles, I'd say that
was a pretty good blindside.
So much for old tribal
loyalties.
This is clearly an individual
game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time
on Survivor:
>> You're going to be the next
to go.
>> PROBST: Sierra fights for her
life.
>> I'm trying to explain my
side so it doesn't look like I
was the mastermind.
>> I don't think you were the
mastermind.
I don't think you're smart
enough for it.
>> PROBST: Can she save herself?
>> You made your bed.
It kills me to have this kid
here asking me to throw her a
bone.
It breaks my heart.
>> I knew at the merge that
what would happen is I'd
become a big target.
I didn't think it'd happen
quite that quickly, um, but it
kind of feels good to
blindside because I wanted to
blindside someone, too.
That's all part of the game.
The thing that Sierra probably
needs most is in my pocket right
now: the hidden immunity idol.
But it doesn't matter.
She'd be next, regardless, to
go.
It's just a matter of time.