>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: at the newly merged
Forza tribe...
...former Timbira members
Coach and Tyson put together
an alliance.
>> That's what I'm talking
about, man.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: And they targeted one
of their own.
While Sierra and Brendan also
tried to pull in the Jalapao
Three.
>> I think we go after Coach.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Setting the stage for
a showdown between Brendan and
Coach.
>> We're cutting the head off
the dragon and sending Brendan
home.
When it comes head-to-head,
we'll see who really was the
Chosen One.
>> PROBST: And the old Jalapao
tribe found themselves in an
unlikely position.
At the immunity challenge:
Getting down to it, it is
Brendan and Tyson.
Tyson won his second immunity
in a row.
And at Tribal Council, Brendan
thought his plan was in the bag.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol, and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
And didn't play his idol.
Brendan.
The old Jalapao tribe sided
with Coach's alliance.
Eighth person voted out and the
first member of our jury:
Brendan.
Blindsiding Brendan, and leaving
Sierra in an alliance of one.
Brendan, the tribe has spoken.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> So how awesome was that?
>> Awesome!
>> Sierra, you got to admit.
>> Yeah, you guys are...
>> Pretty badass.
>> I mean, obviously, I know
I'm the next one to go, so let's
just try to make these next
couple days congenial, I guess.
I mean...
Whatever.
That sucked.
It was probably the worst night
I've ever had out here.
And right now I'm just tired and
kind of hurt, and I kind of just
want to disappear.
Can I please have a conversation
with you, Coach?
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
I don't think I'm a bad person
for writing Coach's name down.
Although, it was a very hard
choice to make.
I have never planned on ever
voting for you.
And I'm being 100% honest with
you.
>> Every decision you made was
bad.
You could have written down
anybody else's in this game that
doesn't have the character like
I have.
>> You're right.
>> Everybody out here has lied
except for me.
Um, I knew that Sierra would
want to assuage her guilt,
massage it.
Make herself feel rationalized
and justified inside.
That's what we do when we make
poor decisions in life.
But you have to realize
something.
In war, and love and war...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...it's kill or be killed.
So you pitted yourself against
me.
Brendan pitted himself against
Who deserves to go next?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> I came down to the water
early this morning to celebrate
the victory over Brendan.
Throughout the entire
meditation, there was this
feeling of peace that just kind
of settled over me and
permeated my every fiber.
For me to pit myself against
somebody who is younger, that
is faster than me, and maybe
stronger than me, although I
bench-press 300 pounds.
And we were talking two days ago
and he was like, "Really?"
'Cause he doesn't do that.
To defeat a worthy opponent
like that, at this stage in the
game-- the piece de résistance.
The dragonslayer has vanquished
the dragon once and for all.
(shouts)
Over!
The battle has already been won.
Victory is mine.
>> Well, it just all started
with the way that I started off
as a rocky start and I latched
on to someone else.
I guess I was blinded, so I'm
not even going to say that I
wasn't.
>> Tribal Council went as
planned.
Brendan didn't have a clue it
was coming.
And, uh, Sierra was really
shocked.
Stephen and I-- we've actually
put ourselves in a really
good position.
And actually, Stephen and I
could've decided who went home
last night, and we decided to
stick through with the warrior
alliance.
And Stephen and I, we're happy
with the way things are going.
We're happy to see Sierra go
next.
>> I guess the unfortunate part
is I didn't make any choices
in it, and I followed along.
>> But that's out of your
character.
>> Right.
>> You say stuff, you know what
I mean?
You jump into any conversation
about anything.
>> He was holding the idol, so,
therefore, I was playing...
>> The most powerful thing is
friends.
>> After last night at Tribal
Council, I guess I'm kind of
pleading for my life.
What sucks the most is that I
was on top of the game
yesterday.
And then today, I'm, like, at
the bottom of the food chain.
But I'm not going to just roll
over and die.
I'm sorry that I made bad
choices.
>> Okay.
>> Everyone's had moments of
betrayal, but I wasn't about
to go on some massacre against
you.
And I wasn't about to go on some
massacre against Coach, and...
>> I like to see Sierra scramble
and mope.
Uh, I think it's funny because
I've never liked Sierra.
To me, she's of no worth.
I mean, her parents probably
love her.
I can't imagine her boyfriend's
that cool.
The thing is, the most important
thing here is trust.
>> I agree with that.
>> And you know what?
It's... everybody here in camp
right now, I get along with.
And I don't feel like anybody's
a snake waiting to bite me.
And you keep scrambling and you
keep backpedaling, and you keep
making excuses about how you
didn't know.
So you can scramble all you
want...
>> I'm not trying to scramble,
Tyson.
I'm trying to explain my side
so it doesn't look like I was
the mastermind behind it.
>> I don't think you were the
mastermind.
I don't think you're smart
enough for it.
Like, really.
>> That's fine.
>> If I would have lost the
challenge yesterday, who would
you have voted for?
>> That was undecided.
I was... as far...
>> Who would you have voted for?
>> J.T.
>> Wrong.
>> That's where my head was at.
>> Brendan would have come to
you and told you to vote for me.
>> And I probably would have
done it.
>> Okay, you probably would
have, and that's what I'm saying
right now.
>> Okay.
>> Okay?
And I'm going to be straight up,
100% honest with you right now.
You're going to be the next
to go.
You're not going to be able
to change that.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's challenge
you will be divided into two
teams of four.
On my go, two members of each
team will race out to collect
a large puzzle board, then race
back, then the next two go.
Once you have all four boards,
you must arrange those boards
in their own specific spots.
Then you will flip and rotate
the boards until all the holes
line up, revealing seven vowels.
Once you have the seven vowels,
you will use the corresponding
tiles on your answer board,
along with the tiles of the
seven consonants that are given
to you.
You'll then combine them all to
form a four-word phrase.
The winning team will be treated
to an afternoon of local
entertainment and local food.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: You will be treated
to a performance of capoeira...
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: ...a beautiful
Brazilian martial art form that
combines dance and music.
It's really pretty spectacular.
You will also enjoy a local
feast.
In addition, the winning team
of four will send one person
from the losing team to Exile
Island.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, we have our two
teams.
Red team: J.T., Erinn, Debbie,
and Tyson.
The Black team: Coach, Stephen,
Sierra, and Taj.
Nice reward on the line.
Survivors ready?
Go!
J.T. and Erinn heading out for
the Red.
Coach and Stephen heading out
for the Black team.
>> Damn, J.T. is so fast.
>> All right, start working on
the knots.
>> PROBST: Untie those boards
and get them back.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: J.T. and Erinn
heading back with their board
for the Red team.
Coach and Stephen heading back
with their first board for the
Black team.
Now you've got to find the right
spot.
Where does that first board go?
>> The last one.
>> PROBST: Good!
Taj and Sierra heading out for
the Black team.
Debbie and Tyson heading out for
the Red team.
Taj and Sierra heading back for
the Black team with their
second board.
Taj is wearing that board,
carrying it on her shoulders.
Debbie and Tyson racing back
with the Red team's second
board.
Find the right slot.
Get it in and the next pair goes
back out.
>> Not that one.
>> Back up, back up.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Coach and Stephen
heading out now.
>> Whoo!
>> Just put it in there!
>> PROBST: Erinn and J.T. back
out on the course for the
Red team.
Two boards left.
Careful, Taj.
Snap your neck.
>> I know.
I couldn't get it any other way.
>> Got it?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah?
>> PROBST: Red team's now in
the lead with their third board.
>> Come on, Coach!
>> Good.
>> PROBST: Debbie and Tyson
looking for that fourth and
final board for the Red team.
Coach and Stephen coming back
now with the third board for
the Black team.
>> Okay, that's it.
>> PROBST: Taj and Sierra now
out on the course looking for
that fourth and final board.
>> PROBST: Tyson and Debbie have
their fourth board.
They're heading back.
Taj and Sierra have their
fourth board.
They're heading back.
>> Put it in, guys!
>> PROBST: Red team back with
that fourth and final board.
>> Come on, girls!
>> PROBST: Taj and Sierra
struggling to get back.
Those boards are heavy.
>> Okay...
>> Upside down.
>> Move it? Upside down.
>> PROBST: Black team, back
with their final board.
Now, got to start eyeballing,
looking down the line at all
these pieces of puzzle board.
>> Nothing, Erinn.
>> PROBST: When you have the
boards in the right position,
they will line up to reveal
vowels.
>> There's nothing.
>> PROBST: You see a vowel
clearly, you have it right.
If your vision is blocked, you
have it wrong.
>> There, there-there, that was
good, good, good!
Leave that one!
Good!
"A's" good, too!
>> We've got "A..."
>> Good, good, good, and good.
We got it, okay.
>> Read the letters.
>> PROBST: Red team thinks they
have it right.
They're working on solving the
puzzle.
>> Flip that.
Flip that and reverse it.
Flip it and reverse it.
>> Once you have the seven
vowels, you will mix those with
the seven consonants and the
punctuation.
Looking for a four-word phrase.
>> Switch it over, the first
one, right?
>> Take this one, flip it.
>> PROBST: Coach, Sierra, Taj,
and Stephen are still trying to
get their boards lined up.
>> Feast, feast, feast, feast.
>> What do you think?
>> I think this one's...
>> No, flip it around.
>> PROBST: Black team taking
forever to get these pieces in
the right order.
Red team made it look easy.
>> Got it!
>> We got it.
>> PROBST: Red team thinks they
have it.
"You've won a feast" is
correct.
Red team wins reward!
Black team never even got
started.
>> Good job, you guys.
>> PROBST: Erinn, Debbie, Tyson,
J.T., nice work.
>> Thank you.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: Before you head out
for your nice reward, big
decision: Taj, Sierra, Stephen,
Coach.
One of the four of them going
to Exile Island.
>> Stephen.
>> PROBST: No question about it.
>> It's my home away from home,
Jeff.
>> Do it, Steve.
Now that Brendan's gone and
his idol's out of play, I feel
like there's a new idol on
Exile, so Stephen needs to be
on Exile to ensure that Sierra
doesn't get the other idol if
there is one placed out.
>> PROBST: Erinn, Debbie, Tyson,
J.T., grab your stuff.
Head out and enjoy the
afternoon.
Coach, you continue to lose out
on these nice rewards.
All that life experience
not helping you out here.
>> You know, I didn't line up
boards like this in the Amazon.
>> PROBST: All right, guys.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Next time, maybe.
>> Hello.
(indistinct chatter)
Hi. Thank you.
>> Thank you. Hey.
>> I was super-excited to win
the challenge 'cause I've never
been on a reward before.
>> Oh, man, look at the food.
>> Just to the left of us was
all this food, and I'm so hungry
today.
This is so perfect.
I really wanted this.
>> Mmm!
>> Oh, my gosh!
Did you get any of this?
>> Mm-hmm. Yes, I did.
>> We look filthy.
We haven't brushed our teeth in
26 days, and then we pile on as
much food as we can on our
plates and we're eating like
savages.
And they're all looking at us
like, "What's wrong with these
people?"
>> We're very hungry.
>> Very hungry.
>> Very, very hungry.
>> Normally, I usually don't eat
like this.
And little children, I love
little children.
I'm a school principal in the
United States.
That's why I was asking about
the children.
As a mother, you know, I miss my
children horribly at home.
And as a principal, I miss all
of you know, my 908 Drake
Middle School kids.
So immediately, I just
gravitated towards these little
boys.
You're beautiful.
You're a very handsome man.
(laughter)
Yeah.
I don't think I'll ever take my
job for granted anymore 'cause
I've been without it, and I've
always loved it, but I realize
how much I love those kids that
I work with.
>> Dueling banjos, okay.
>> That's really cool.
(singing in Portuguese)
>> Capoeira is a Brazilian
form of martial arts, but they
don't actually make any physical
contact.
They look like they're fighting,
but it's also a dance.
and then they started pulling us
up and teaching us how to do
the dance along with them.
(cheering)
>> After we had eaten all that
food, you're so stuffed you
can't move, and then we've got
these people that are like,
"No, come, come, dance with us."
I'm like, "Okay, do a little
dance.
Fine, no big deal."
But once I sat down again, oh,
man, it was terrible.
I way overdid it.
Gross, I just threw up on my
feet.
I was like the little kid that
eats pizza and ice cream and,
like, gets in, like, the
playland balls and jumps around
a bunch, and then can't
understand why they threw up.
It was terrible.
>> Brendan left with the idol
in his pocket last night, and
it could just be that there's a
second idol out there and
nobody knows where it is.
So I am hoping to find a clue
to a new idol.
And I would end up with two
idols in my possession,
This looks like a big piece of
paper.
Which could it might mean?
Oh, no.
It's clue #7, which means
there's no new idol, which
means I'm here for nothing.
Oh, well.
I'm lucky I'm not on that
reward.
Who wants to be feasting when
they could be... in sand?
Thank God I have no food and
bleak surroundings for a couple
of days, you know?
(cawing)
>> You and... and Coach and
Tyson had an alliance?
Does that make you bad people?
>> No, but if we would have
messed up and, and gotten the
wrong thing in the game, then I
expect to just...
"Yeah, I did wrong. I'm sorry."
>> I didn't know.
>> Who do you think needs to go
then?
Everybody else has been loyal.
Who goes, if not you?
There's reactions to actions.
You chose the wrong action, and,
I mean, I love you to death.
I care about you.
I don't like to have to vote
you off.
>> You think what just happened
to you guys was a huge deal?
You have no flippin' clue how
many people are going to do that
to you guys.
Later down the road, there will
be a moment where you will
regret this.
>> Prob... okay, maybe.
But I have got an alliance now,
and you've got to understand,
I've got to play the game, too,
Sierra.
>> Now I'm in limbo.
That puts me even more in an
insecure position.
>> Okay.
>> That's the choice you made.
>> Like I says, it's not against
you personally...
Oh, now, you get to decide?
You wanted to talk to me, now
you want to decide when it's
over?
>> I wanted to talk to you in a
nonconfrontational level where
people weren't interjecting.
>> Okay, so you're done with me?
>> I'm done with fighting.
I'm done with everyone.
(crying): You know, I'm getting
kicked in the face.
>> No one's kicking you in the
face.
Why do you think that?
>> Because it's just ironic...
>> Because we're not saying what
you want to hear.
>> ...how you're going to keep
around other liars.
There's other...?
>> Who's the other liars?
>> I'm not talking to you,
Erinn.
>> I'm just asking who you're
talking about.
If there's liars amongst us,
I'd like to know who they are.
>> Well, you'd be the last
person that I'd tell.
>> Oh, so it's like that?
Well, I mean, we're just all
kind of like... you're saying
the same thing over and over and
over again.
And, like, I think we're just
done hearing it.
>> Okay.
As much as Sierra just annoys me
to death, and I think that she's
so dumb, she's right.
Everything she said is totally
true.
Once Sierra's no longer with
us, the game will change.
And I am the one that's going
to, like, turn all of this on
its head.
Guilty as charged.
>> Hey, Coach.
All I wanted to say was, if you
were me, would you just roll
over and take it?
I mean, yeah, I could just roll
over and accept it, but then I
guess I wouldn't be me, and I
guess you wouldn't expect me to
do something like that 'cause
you'd probably expect more out
of me.
I was never going to go hurt
anyone that I really cared
about, and...
>> Except for me.
>> But if... if given, like...
I mean, I'm not asking for one,
but I'm saying if it sounds
practical, if it even sounds
possible, given another chance,
I would prove I am a good
person.
I am a loyal person.
But if I gave up on myself
right now, like I want to, I
just want to go home, I do.
I don't want to be around a
whole bunch of people that...
that I hurt.
But I don't want to go out like
that.
>> But I mean, if you're asking
me would I like to give you
a second chance?
Of course I'd like to give you
a second chance.
Am I going to you a second
chance?
Probably not.
This is what I think.
The honorable thing is
to accept your fate, not try
to make deals with people.
And the samurai warrior, if he
did dishonor to himself or his
family, you know what he would
do?
He would fall on his sword.
Death before dishonor.
You can't change the inevitable.
>> You really want to see Erinn
stay here over me?
>> No, but you made your bed.
>> Would I be Strong Sierra if
I didn't have this conversation
with you?
No.
Would you be Coach, the one who
pushed up against me to make me
work harder at challenges if
you didn't think that I had
that in me?
No.
So don't get mad at me for
having this conversation with
you.
>> You know, the coach in me is
continually looking to those
that are in need of assistance
or encouragement.
So I see somebody like Sierra,
my heart just goes out to her.
>> How do you save the kind
enemy?
>> That kills me to have this
kid here asking me to throw her
a bone because she's going
through so much trials.
It breaks my heart.
>> Would you give up, Coach, if
you made the wrong choice?
There is a very, very small
glimmer of hope, but I most
definitely need to win immunity.
I feel it's my only chance of
pulling through this.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Stephen,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Stephen!
>> Hello.
Oh, I missed you guys.
I miss body warmth is what I
missed.
>> Get in here.
We missed you.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: First things first,
Tyson, take back the necklace.
Tyson has had this both times
it's been up for grabs.
Will he get it a third time?
For today's challenge, you're
going to take part in the
Survivor version of
shuffleboard.
You'll each have three pucks.
You'll slide your pucks across
the board with one simple goal:
the person whose puck ends up
closest to the center of the "X"
wins immunity, and guaranteed
a one-in-seven shot at winning
the million dollars.
Losers goes to Tribal Council
where somebody will be voted
out of this game.
There is a twist to today's
challenge.
If you feel so confident that
you don't think you need
immunity, you can skip
participating in the challenge
and instead...
>> Oh, no...
>> PROBST: ...you can eat.
(jubilant shouting)
>> PROBST: You're each going to
get a rock.
Take a rock.
>> Oh, my God, thank you!
>> PROBST: There's no looking.
The rock doesn't mean anything
at this point.
If you want to eat, you're
going to show me that rock.
If you want to play, you're
going to show me an empty hand.
Everybody put your hands out.
And reveal.
Stephen says he's going to eat.
J.T. says he's going to eat.
Coach says he's going to eat.
>> So Coach is hungry enough
to quit a game and eat pizza.
When do I get my pizza, dude?
I've been winning all these
challenges, you know?
They should let me have pizza
and not worry about sealing the
deal to get rid of Sierra.
>> PROBST: Those of you eating,
take a spot at the table.
Everybody else, we will draw
for our order and we'll get
started.
All right, we have our order.
This challenge is set to begin.
J.T., Steve, and Coach, you guys
can eat for as long as the
challenge goes.
Start eating.
Sierra, you're first up.
Everybody will have three shots
and we will rotate the order
every round so that nobody is
ever stuck in the same position.
Sierra, a little short.
>> Hmm.
>> PROBST: Debbie now up with
her first shot.
Debbie, a little short.
There's a learning curve to
this.
(grunting)
Use that cold energy and that
shiver.
Taj goes a little long.
Erinn with her first shot.
Nobody having much luck yet.
All Tyson does is block the
road for everybody else.
Second round: this time,
Debbie, you will go first.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: First round didn't
yield much.
Debbie with a nice shot.
>> Whoo!
>> Come on, Debbie.
>> PROBST: Debbie is now the
closest.
Taj with her second shot.
Tyson gets a bump from Taj.
Tyson is now the mark to beat.
Erinn is up.
Erinn slides inside of Tyson.
Erinn is now the closest.
Tyson now with his second shot.
>> Good job, Erinn.
>> PROBST: Tyson, once again,
blocks the road.
Sierra now with her second shot.
She's going to have to get past
Tyson to get a shot at it.
Sierra moves Tyson into the
lead.
After two rounds, Tyson is the
closest to the "X."
Everybody has one shot left.
Taj will be first up.
>> I can't focus.
Oh!
>> PROBST: Taj, nothing but a
sand dune.
>> Oh, I should have ate.
>> PROBST: Erinn's now up.
Erinn knocks out Sierra's
closest puck.
Tyson now up.
Tyson, your last shot.
Tyson increases his lead.
>> Tyson!
>> PROBST: Tyson still the mark
to beat.
Sierra is up.
Sierra, you know what you need
to do.
You need to get closer to that
"X" than Tyson.
Sierra knocks Tyson out and
puts herself in position to win
this challenge.
Sierra is now the mark to beat.
Huge move.
>> When Sierra was doing her
little dance, I was just like,
"I might have screwed everything
up."
Should I have been out there
competing?
Yeah, I should have been.
>> PROBST: Debbie is now up with
her last shot.
>> Oh, Lord.
>> PROBST: This is it.
It comes down to this.
Sierra will walk away with
immunity unless Debbie can land
closer to that "X."
And she does.
>> Debbie!
>> PROBST: Debbie wins
individual immunity.
(cheering)
This challenge is over.
Drop it, Stephen.
Finish what's in your mouth.
That's it.
Debbie, come on over.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> Debbie!
>> PROBST: Middle school
principal has a one-in-seven
shot of winning this game.
Debbie cannot be voted out
at tonight's Tribal Council.
As for the rest of you, after
27 days, one of you going home
tonight.
Grab your stuff.
I'll see you at Tribal Council.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> What I needed to do today
was win that immunity challenge,
and it didn't happen.
So a part of me is like, "Maybe
that's my fate."
But there's a large part of me
that prays for a miracle.
>> Debbie, if I would've known
you were going to win, I would
have sat down and eaten half
a slice.
>> I know.
>> I'm excited.
I wanted to win one immunity,
at least.
>> And there's nothing awesomer
than seeing somebody celebrate
before the game is over.
>> Yeah.
>> I would have liked to have
the immunity necklace again.
I thought it would be pretty
badass if I would have worn it
for a third time.
But tonight's Tribal Council is
going to be awesome.
Um, I'm hoping that Sierra will
cry a lot.
>> I do not want to go to
Tribal in the rain.
>> Oh, God.
>> Yeah.
>> That's true.
>> I mean, this is, like the
time.
It's like opportunity's
knocking.
What the hell are we-- you know?
>> I know.
>> See, get... talk to J.T.
Let me know what y'all want to
do.
I'm willing to do whatever y'all
want to do.
You're a hundred percent with
us, right?
Okay, okay.
>> Tyson is such a physical
competitor, that he may win
every challenge out here.
We got lucky today and someone
else won, so we have to get rid
of Tyson.
Um, and this might just be the
chance to do it.
It could be Tyson or Sierra
tonight.
This is not an easy decision.
But I know that there's no way
I can win this game by just
kind of hanging out and letting
other people make my decisions.
This move is potentially a very
pivotal one.
>> I wouldn't worry.
>> I'd hate to make it this
early 'cause we don't want to
get stuck with Sierra.
>> You know it happens.
It happens every season.
Someone goes on a run.
Let's make it you.
>> It'd be a lot safer,
wouldn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> No.
Sierra is.
>> Sierra is a lying bitch and
I hate her.
>> I hate her, too.
>> I want to get her away from
my face, dude.
If we stick through with this
plan that we're talking about
now-- Stephen, myself, Erinn,
and Taj.
If we get rid of Tyson, we could
do it without talking to Sierra
'cause we have the numbers, but
it's going to go against the
warrior alliance that Coach has
worked so hard to build here.
So it's going to be a tough
decision.
>> We going to recap the plan.
>> Okay.
>> Sierra's going tonight,
no-brainer.
>> Okay.
>> One of my top priorities
right now at this point is to
go to the five with the warrior
alliance.
It would be ... stupid if we
made an alliance, gave it a
name, bandied the name about,
talked about ourselves being
warriors, and then chickened out
at the last second.
I know I can trust you and
that's so important to me, man.
>> You have my word.
>> There you go.
>> It's really going to crush
Coach if I go through with this
move to get rid of Tyson.
It's really going to crush him.
I don't know what I'm going to
do, man.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the first member of our jury.
Brendan, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
At the last Tribal Council,
Brendan was blindsided.
Sierra, you looked stunned.
>> Uh, yeah, and, unfortunately,
I'll probably go home due to the
choices that I made, but if it's
my time, it's my time, and, uh,
no one here is blindsiding me
today.
>> PROBST: Tyson, in spite of
not having immunity tonight,
concerned it could be you, or
are you feeling pretty
comfortable tonight?
>> Yeah, I'm feeling pretty
comfortable.
The people I've aligned myself
with are the people I trust.
I'm also happy that Debbie won.
When you can't win yourself,
it's nice to see someone you
love win.
>> Thank you, Tyson.
>> PROBST: J.T., a little hard
to hear that?
Tyson saying, "Well, if I can't
win, I'm glad Debbie won."
He didn't say, "I'm glad..."
>> Well, I said "someone I
love."
It's not to say she's the only
one I love here.
>> PROBST: Who else do you love
here?
>> Um, Debbie, Coach, Stephen,
Taj, Erinn, J.T., Brendan.
>> PROBST: So your vote's pretty
clear.
You're voting Sierra.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Sierra, do you think
people are telling you you're
going to be voted out because
they want to appear nice, so
that when you're on the jury,
you'll consider voting for them
if they make it to the end?
>> No, it was kind of obvious
the moment that Brendan went
out that I was next.
What I was trying to tell them
was that in the alliance that I
made with someone else, I
probably spoke to that person
about what we were planning on
doing...
>> PROBST: I don't know what
you're talking about.
>> What do you mean?
>> Nobody does.
>> Tyson!
>> I know what she's saying.
You want me to explain it?
>> No, I don't need you to
explain it for me, Tyson.
What I'm explaining is...
>> PROBST: What's going on
between you and Tyson?
>> Tyson always likes to badger
me, and that's the way that
Tyson is.
He's kind of a smartass.
I don't think half the things
he has to say are very funny.
But he's never been really nice
to me and that's fine.
>> PROBST: Tyson, is that true?
Have you and Sierra butted
heads from the beginning?
>> I've never really felt a
close bond with Sierra.
I mean, tried to be friendly
and cordial, but when I'm done
listening to her talk, I'm done
listening.
>> PROBST: Are you concerned at
all that that kind of an
attitude could cost in this
game?
>> I told her I'd give her five
minutes and I did.
And she kept going.
And, I mean, I was irritated at
what her and Brendan had tried
to do.
So I don't know why I need
to give her all the courtesy
and she give me none.
>> Um, well, this is a game
about strengths and weaknesses.
It's not a personality contest.
The thing is, he's really strong
in challenges, and if you want
to take someone strong all the
way to the final two, like, so
be it.
But he is really strong.
I wouldn't be voting him out
because we didn't get along as
two people.
I'd be voting him out so that I
could win a reward challenge or
so that someone else that I
aligned with could win another
challenge.
It's just the way that the game
works.
>> Coach, Sierra brings up a
good point.
Tyson won the first two
immunity challenges.
He doesn't have immunity
tonight.
Is he a threat?
And if so, why not take him out
tonight?
>> I've said from the very
beginning that I wanted to walk
the path of the noble warrior
and finding that great
competition that you can pit
yourself against.
>> PROBST: And then you voted
out Brendan.
>> Yeah.
>> I will explain this to you.
>> PROBST: I'm sure you will.
>> Because Brendan pitted
himself against me.
If it's war, one-on-one...
>> PROBST: I thought that's what
you wanted?
>> Exactly, and I won.
Thank you.
Exactly.
I outsmarted him.
I outfoxed him, and at the
moment, sorry to say, I'm
outleading him.
>> PROBST: Okay.
>> So I won that battle.
Now, as far as the other people,
if I'm going to have trust in
this tribe, we are going to be
on the same page.
And we are going to battle each
other in an honorable fashion.
If I give them my word, I'm not
going to go back on that.
>> PROBST: So an honorable
battle to you then means as long
as we both agree on how we're
going to play this, I'll battle
you.
>> Absolutely.
I will be a ravenous wolf for
anybody that wants to go
head-to-head with me, and I will
cut them off at the knees with
no remorse and no regret.
>> PROBST: J.T., what do you
make of having the best "battle
it out to the end"?
>> Coach said he was going to
change the game.
He's definitely changing it.
I've never seen anyone take the
best competitors to the end.
When he gives me his word,
I take it to the bank.
There's no doubt about it.
>> PROBST: Coach, if J.T. gives
you his word, do you take it to
the bank?
>> The first time I looked in
J.T.'s eyes and I shook his
hand, I knew that where he comes
from, that meant something.
And I see honesty and trust.
And I see a warrior in battle.
That's somebody, obviously, that
I respect and I believe a
hundred percent when he tells me
something.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
get to the vote.
Debbie, you have immunity.
You can give that up to
somebody else or keep it for
yourself.
>> I think I'll wear it proudly
tonight.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Debbie.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Tyson, you're up.
>> Last week, Sierra, I slayed
the dragon.
This week I had to take care of
his bride.
Good night, sweet princess.
>> You're a jerk.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote... Sierra.
Tyson.
Sierra.
Two votes Sierra;
one vote Tyson.
Sierra.
Three votes Sierra;
one vote Tyson.
Tyson.
Three votes Sierra;
two votes Tyson.
Tyson.
We're tied.
That's three votes Sierra;
three votes Tyson.
Tyson.
That's four votes Tyson;
three votes Sierra.
One vote left.
Ninth person voted out and the
second member of our jury:
Tyson.
You need to bring me your torch.
Tyson, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Another Tribal Council,
another blindside.
This is shaping up to be a
battle to the end.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> We're taking out all our
people, and you and I are
sitting ducks.
>> PROBST: Timbira tries to
regroup.
>> It would be you, me, Sierra,
and Erinn?
>> Coach, I think that's the
only way.
>> PROBST: But find themselves
at Sierra's mercy.
>> I thought you said you were
going to be loyal?
>> Then you wrote my name down
last night.
>> I'm going to ask you this
again, Sierra: where's your
loyalty right now?
>> Sneaky bastards.
Now I know how Brendan feels.
Yeah, it was a big shock.
I thought I had my game in the
bag, but I should've probably
not been quite as confident or
so, uh, gullible.
Good luck to everybody.
I guess everybody deserves to
be there.
You beat me.
That's a huge accomplishment.
That bothers me that Sierra will
be here longer than me.
A little weird being outfoxed by
an idiot, but I'm not crying
over it.