>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> Erinn's with us.
She just feels like none of them
care about her, so why should
she care about them?
>> PROBST: The Jalapao Three
pulled in Erinn and took control
of the game, but Coach still
wanted to call the shots.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: However, not everyone
was on board.
>> Hmm-mm.
>> PROBST: Despite Taj and
Erinn's rogue votes...
>> I couldn't vote for Sierra.
>> PROBST: ...Coach got his way.
Sierra, the tribe has spoken.
Six are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Well, final six, guys.
Congratulations.
>> That's not a small
accomplishment.
>> I am so tired.
>> I'm glad the drama's gone.
>> Amen.
I just hope we can get some
sleep tonight.
>> Erinn and Taj took the
cowardly way out and voted for
two people who didn't deserve
to be voted for: Stephen and
Debbie.
It was preposterous.
Erinn and Taj need to be cut
off at the kneecaps.
I'm pissed at them for writing
your name down and for writing
Stephen's name down tonight.
That was ridiculous.
>> You've got to let it go.
>> This is the time for the
warrior alliance.
There's a reason why we have a
name.
People that don't play this game
even half as honestly as me,
even half as bold as me, like we
saw tonight, pisses me off.
I have two words for you.
Taj and Erinn.
You know what?
We're going to run them through
with a sword the next two votes.
And I'm thinking Taj has to go
next.
>> You got to let it go or it's
going to drive you nuts.
>> What a bunch of freaking
cowards.
I'm so pissed at them.
>> All right, I'm going to go
back in there 'cause I don't
want them to think we're out
here.
All right, I'll see you
tomorrow.
>> I just wanted to tell you
that I was backing you up on the
fact that they were cowardly
lions.
>> Coach does not let things go.
without a complete, utter
dialogue as to why.
It gets so old.
He called me over to talk.
He's really upset.
I said, "I know, but it's over."
You know?
>> I don't care about the
million dollars.
I care about my integrity and
honesty and changing this game
from start to finish, and I've
said that from day one, and
that will never change.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
>> Coach and I have been
together since day one, but
lately, it's been not a positive
thing for me.
>> Jet, come here.
>> Jet.
As a social person in a social
game, it is not good for me to
be attached to Coach.
He's a downer.
People are tired of comments
and directives and not doing a
whole lot around camp, really
hadn't been for a while.
So, I laid in bed last night,
and it came to me and I thought,
you know what?
I got to step up.
Hey.
>> Sounds fishy.
>> Things are coming out that I
didn't sign up for, and I think
that you guys probably feel the
same.
You know what I'm saying?
We're going to have to talk.
>> I love him.
>> I love him, too, but we'll
have to...
>> Yeah.
>> Debbie is playing a very
strategical game, and she's
scared right now, and, uh,
Debbie may be more of a loose
cannon than I thought.
Debbie may be up to some no good
around here.
I'm so sick of Debbie.
>> I'm starting to really
dislike her.
(imitating Debbie): J.T., you
gonna saw this with me?
You think it's going to rain
today?
>> (imitating Debbie): I think
it's clearing up.
>> J.T...
>> I guess you're talking about
me.
What's going on, guys?
Hey, I don't know what you all
have been talking about, but I
don't want Coach speaking for
me.
Now, I will tell you this, and I
don't like going against Coach,
but as far as I'm concerned,
I'm on a tribe with you two and
I'm in an alliance with you two,
and I give you my honest
to God, pinky swear word on
that, God strike me dead.
(thunder rumbles)
I am in it with you two.
>> All right, good, okay.
>> Good, good.
>> Good, all right.
>> I love you, Debbie.
>> And then we're going to go
party in Biloxi.
I love you.
I'm so glad you're in my life.
>> I know.
>> Debbie is a very strategic
player, and I think people don't
give her enough credit because
she is sweet and because she is
chattery, but she has definitely
got a lot going on underneath
that persona, and she worries me
a little bit.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Welcome to the Survivor
Auction.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: You each have 500
US dollars.
Bidding will be in $20
increments.
You cannot share money.
You cannot share food.
Ready for the first item?
>> Yup.
>> Yup, ready.
>> Oh, my God, french fries!
>> PROBST: Big bowl of french
fries.
>> 40 bucks.
>> PROBST: 40 to Taj.
>> $50.
>> PROBST: $20 increments.
>> Uh, $70.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: $20.
You're a principal, not a math
teacher.
It's okay.
>> My math teachers will tell
you that, too.
Whatever.
I want to go up on Taj.
>> PROBST: $60 to Debbie.
>> $80.
>> PROBST: $80 to Coach.
>> $100.
>> PROBST: $100 for a bowl of
fries.
>> I'll pay $120.
>> PROBST: $120 going once,
twice, sold.
Next item:
chicken parmesan.
>> Oh, wow!
>> PROBST: With garlic bread,
glass of red wine.
Civilized eating.
>> 100 bucks.
>> 100 bucks to Coach.
>> $120.
>> PROBST: $120 to Stephen.
>> $200.
>> PROBST: $200 to Coach.
>> $300.
>> Oh!
>> God, that's bad.
>> PROBST: $300 to J.T.
>> $320.
>> PROBST: $320 to Coach.
Going once, going twice...
Sold to Coach, $320.
>> You hesitated there just a
little bit, didn't you, Jeff?
You hesitated before you put it
down.
>> Just go eat.
>> PROBST: Next item.
It will remain covered.
>> $100.
>> $120.
>> $140.
>> $160.
>> PROBST: J.T. at 160.
Going once, twice, sold to J.T.
for $160.
>> Oh, I'm crossing my fingers
for you, buddy.
>> This is what you got.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Nachos, guacamole,
salsa.
>> PROBST: Next item will
remain covered.
>> $20.
$20 to Stephen.
>> $40.
>> $60.
>> $80.
>> $100.
>> PROBST: J.T., you're done?
>> I mean, it's hard letting
that go for $100.
I mean...
>> PROBST: You don't even know
what it is and it's hard to let
it go.
>> I'll let it go for Stephen.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Going once, twice,
sold to Stephen, $100.
>> Chocolate cake for you,
Steve-o.
>> This is a delicacy in...
>> Oh, no.
>> PROBST: In Brazil.
Chicken hearts.
(screaming)
>> All right, I love chicken
hearts.
Mmm.
>> PROBST: You ever had a
chicken heart before?
>> No, but I'm loving it.
I'm feeling my own heart
increasing in volume.
This is big.
>> Are they any good?
(laughing)
>> PROBST: Last item.
>> What?
>> Last item?
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: This is a Samsung
Instinct by Sprint.
This phone does a lot.
One thing it can do right now
is bring you love from home.
Loaded on this phone are
messages from your loved ones.
You are going to be bidding on
a chance to see the video
message that your loved one sent
to you.
Only one person can buy this
and win this.
But for this item, you can pool
money, meaning if somebody
wants to give you their money,
they can.
Let's start the bidding.
>> Here, Taj.
>> PROBST: For the Samsung
Instinct by Sprint.
Loved one's messages from home.
Everybody is giving their money
to Taj.
>> That's so sweet.
>> PROBST: What does that say
about this group of six in a
game that can be rather nasty
at times?
>> Taj has had a tougher time
than the rest of us.
Debbie has kids, but Taj left a
little baby at home.
>> PROBST: Taj, you're not even
going to have to bid against
anybody.
>> I know.
You guys, I love you to death
for giving me this.
>> You just go enjoy it.
You need it.
>> PROBST: All right, Taj, let
me officially put it up for bid.
The Sprint loved one message
from home.
$20?
>> I want it. I want it.
What are you giving me, 20
bucks, your card?
>> Everything.
>> PROBST: You don't need to
give me all.
Well, here.
>> PROBST: $20.
All right, Taj.
Get that so you can see it.
>> Hey, babe.
Wait for number one, two, and
three, and four.
No, I'm just kidding.
We're all here wanting to say
hello to you.
We miss you so much.
As you can see, the house is
not the same without you.
We are sending you out
much love and energy.
We're praying for you every
single day.
You have any concerns of
anything going on here, no,
we've got it locked down.
So you just put all your focus
and attention on your task at
hand.
We're holding it down here at
the George household.
See you back at the camp.
(smooching loudly)
(sobbing)
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Did you hear that
last line?
>> I did.
>> PROBST: There's one line on
there, might have been a little
hard to hear.
There's one...
>> See you back at the camp!
Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God.
>> What?!
>> PROBST: Just dawned on her.
>> Oh, my God!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
>> That's wonderful.
>> Oh, my God!
Can we go now?
>> PROBST: Taj, come on back up
here.
I'll tell you how it's going to
work.
So the last thing Eddie said on
this tape was, "I'll see you
back at camp."
Which means just what you
think it does.
The bad news is he's the only
loved one that's coming back to
camp, but everyone can have a
loved one back at camp if
you're willing to make a
sacrifice.
If instead of taking Eddie back
to camp, you will instead send
yourself to Exile Island, where
Eddie will come with you...
>> Oh! Oh!
>> PROBST: Then everybody else
gets a loved one back at camp.
>> I'll do it!
I'll do it!
>> Yeah, baby!
>> I'll do it.
>> Okay, can we go now?
>> A romantic night in the
dunes.
Are you crazy?
>> Exactly.
>> PROBST: Here's a map.
Not that you need it.
>> Where do I go?
>> PROBST: Right up this way.
>> Bye, guys.
Have fun.
>> Have fun, Taj.
>> Thank you, Taj!
>> PROBST: Taj will return back
into the game in time for the
next immunity challenge.
I know you guys are ready to
get back to camp.
Grab your stuff.
Get out of here.
Have a good afternoon.
>> Thanks, Jeff!
(screaming)
(laughing)
>> Oh, missing you, babe!
Missing you!
>> Oh, baby!
>> Golly, you look bad.
(laughing)
>> I do. Look at that.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I've been wearing this dress
for a month.
My husband jumps out from
behind a tree and he just
looked like an angel.
He just looked like a big old
muscle-bound... I just wanted to
take him to the side to have a
conjugal visit.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Look at my back.
Look at me legs.
They've been killing me.
I'm like the bugs' favorite
treat out here.
>> Golly, you've lost so much
weight!
>> I don't eat.
>> She looks great.
I mean, she looks... she looks
happy, you know.
She doesn't look withered or
worn down.
She's dirty now.
She smells filthy, you know, but
there's something about the
wild, you know, that make you
sexy, you know.
It's kind of a turn-on, you
know?
This is all right.
>> Funky D, what's up?!
>> Oh, my God.
There's my daughter.
There's my baby.
>> Oh, my God, I am so happy to
see you!
>> Awesome!
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God!
I don't want you to have to see.
>> I was crying.
>> Like my home?
>> I am so gross.
You're going to need to
disinfect yourself.
>> As soon as I saw my brother
standing there with his hand
over his mouth.
>> Oh, my God!
>> It was just like shock at
seeing me.
>> Oh, my God!
>> I just, like, gave him a big
hug.
I mean it was maybe one of the
like most just biggest,
sincerest, like, warmest hug
we've ever shared, like, if
not the most.
>> What do you think of this
place?
Can you believe I've lived here
31 days?
>> I cannot say. It's...
No.
>> Pretty river, isn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> When I saw Adrianna, she was
crying.
It was real huge.
I mean, it was like, I didn't
care about nothing.
I just had to get with my
little sister, you know.
Put it on.
I want to see it.
>> All right.
>> That looks nice on you.
>> You look great.
You look healthy.
You look thin.
>> Don't eat me!
>> I sleep right here.
Those are my pants.
Here's my stuff.
My dad was proud of me just for
coming out here.
>> Now you know that's all you
need.
>> Yeah.
He was like, "Wait a minute.
You're doing this.
What the hell?"
Like, I'm always dressed up.
I'm always super girly and,
like, I think for him to see me
outside of that was a
little bit shocking to him.
>> Hey, man, guess what they
call me in this game?
Dragonslayer because I'm
slaying all the dragons.
I'm running this freaking show,
let me tell you that right now.
I think I'll be in the final
two.
>> I hope so.
>> Unless something crazy comes
up.
If you were to say you could
have filet mignon or you can see
your assistant coach for ten
minutes, I would say I want to
see my assistant coach.
(back cracking)
Ah.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking
about.
Get this, too.
Yeah, no, push, forward, more.
We are not doing weird sexual
positions, by the way.
It's just I haven't had my back
cracked.
>> What is that?
>> Corongutoba.
You can make tortillas out of
it.
>> You can?
Mm-hmm. Here, try it.
>> Suck on the pit for a while.
Don't break your teeth.
>> Smells like dirty feet, kind
of.
>> That's my favorite snack
we got.
>> You don't have to finish it.
I know.
We love it.
>> Mm.
>> And another thing you have
to be careful of out here is
like the scorpions and stuff
like to hide under the branches
so you be careful where you
grab it.
>> Scorpions, huh?
>> Yeah.
>> Underneath where?
>> They're more afraid of you
than you of them.
>> I don't want to find out.
You know what, I played ball.
I played against great Steeler
defenses; I played against
great players like Ray Lewis,
but, oh, snakes, scorpions,
spiders... I'm like, "What?!
You live with... these are your
friends now?"
>> Look at you!
That's my man!
Okay.
Let's get some on there.
Keep it going.
>> I have a newfound respect
for her doing this for 31 days,
and not any help and standing
strong.
I know plenty of women that
wouldn't even think about
coming out here and enduring
this.
So, you know, she gets all of
my love for this one.
She's the best.
>> I'll be home soon.
>> This is your half...
not halftime.
This is the fourth-quarter prep.
>> Seeing my husband just,
just... it really helped me.
He is my fire.
He is the love of my life.
So it was just like the skies
just parted; the sun came out.
I just... and nothing else hurt
after that.
>> You're doing great, man.
You're doing amazingly.
>> It's okay.
>> Huh?
>> I just hate breaking down.
>> Why?
>> You know, it's like you're
not... you don't think about
these things, but when I'm out
here I don't think about that...
I try not to think about the
people I'm missing at home.
>> They're good.
She told me to tell you that she
loves you.
And wants to know when you're
getting back.
>> I never thought I'd miss you
and Mom and Jamie so much.
>> Wishing you could be with
the cows.
>> I know, me, too.
>> And I'm so glad I did it
because it's changed...
it's changed me to be a better
person, to not take things for
granted.
Look at my hands.
>> It's okay.
That will all fix.
>> Today has been the most
emotional day for my husband
and I.
It just showed how really
intense our love is for each
other.
It meant the world to me that
my husband came out here to
support me.
I didn't want him to go, though.
>> Very cool thing, like, I've
definitely changed a lot.
I'm a total badass.
That's all I have to say about
that.
Now when I go home, like,
there's somebody that I don't
have to explain this to.
And to have somebody here that
you can just tell everything
to, and know that he wouldn't
use anything against you.
Somebody who loves you no
matter what.
Somebody's who's worried about
you, somebody who's concerned
about you, was a really great
thing.
Out here you kind of forget
what that feels like, and it's
really nice.
>> It's good to meet you, Dave.
>> Good to meet you, J.T.,
and good luck to you.
>> Absolutely.
>> Hey.
You've got a good woman.
She cares a lot about you.
>> Thanks.
>> She does.
I mean that.
>> I'm so glad everybody was
here.
>> I don't want you all to go.
>> I know, I know.
>> Okay, bye.
>> Good to meet you, Coach.
>> You, too.
>> Good luck to you.
>> Thank you.
>> Please don't tell Mom how
skinny I am.
Oh, I had a tough time saying
good-bye.
It was really, really hard
to let go of him.
All I can see is my dad, and I
just want to be there, and I
want to hang out with him,
and it was awesome.
>> I love you.
>> I love you, too.
>> Oh!
I can't wait to come home.
>> I'm so proud of you.
>> Thank you.
>> You're the best, you know
that?
>> Yes.
(laughter)
>> I love you.
>> I love you more.
I won't smell like this for
long.
>> I know.
That's okay.
I love you.
>> I love you!
>> Don't let the bedbugs bite!
>> Too late!
>> Cool today.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Kind of cool this morning.
>> Yeah, it is.
Day 32.
Can't believe that.
>> So when he's on a walk
today, let's try to figure out
how we can get out because I
came up with some other ideas,
too.
>> Okay.
>> Things we need to think of
down the line.
>> Right, okay.
Debbie's opened up like white
on rice in the past few days.
And that leads me to believe
that she's turning her game face
on.
She's throwing Coach under the
bus right now, and they've been
tight since day one.
You gotta watch out for people
like that.
>> ...Good to always be
talking strategy and stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, I really think Taj needs
to go.
I have this gut feeling, I keep
thinking that if she plays the
immunity idol, then one of us
could go home.
You see what I'm saying?
I'm not trying to get paranoid,
but I just don't want any wild
cards sneaking up on us, you
know what I'm saying?
Does that sound like a plan?
>> That sounds like a plan.
>> All right, I'm not trying to
push, uh, Taj down your throat.
I want you to feel comfortable
about that.
>> No, I understand completely.
>> I just have a feeling about
it, man.
>> Yeah, we'll do that.
We'll talk with Stephen today.
We can't let Taj in our ear
anymore.
>> Uh-uh.
>> I'm going to go get some more
wood.
>> Coach's strategy's not the
same as mine at this point in
the game.
I feel like I'm really like a
few steps ahead of Coach
when it comes to strategy.
I tell him what he wants to
hear at this point to make it
look like I'm on the same page
he's on, when in turn, you know,
we're not really on the same
page right now.
>> I just feel like, you know,
exactly, like I said...
>> Okay, wait.
Do you agree, Erinn?
>> Yeah.
Yeah, I agree.
>> Um, he definitely don't do
nothing around camp.
>> And also, I think I'm just
ready to see him go.
>> Yeah.
>> It's going to have to be
like we did, like y'all did with
Tyson.
It's got to be a blindside.
>> Right.
>> Sure.
>> But it has to be every
single one of us writing it
down.
>> Yeah.
>> He's going to be furious
or devastated more.
But he's going to feel mostly
betrayed by me.
Talk is, and this is going to
break his heart and he's going
to feel like I have definitely
betrayed him, but the talk is
for Coach to be the next one to
go.
So, he's going to think we're
voting off Taj.
>> Yep.
>> That's who Coach will think
we're voting for.
>> Exactly.
>> Okay.
>> He's pretty much driving
everybody crazy in the camp
right now, including me at
times.
Coach thinks he's in an
alliance with myself, J.T., and
Stephen.
But J.T. and Stephen have had it
as well.
>> At least in the next vote,
we gotta be secure in what we
do.
>> Okay, I think we need to go
ahead and kick Coach out 'cause
he's driving everybody insane.
Honestly, you are two of the
people that I care most about
in this whole thing and I will
do anything in my power for you
two to be sitting there at the
very end.
I swear to you.
I swear to God I will.
And honestly, I'll even do this
for y'all.
If I have the immunity idol,
and it's down to us three,
I will give it to one of you
so I can be voted out.
>> Wow.
>> And I mean that.
I'm happy with third.
Swear to God.
I would hand it to you, J.T.
>> That's awesome, Debbie.
You're an incredible person.
>> I would do it.
I swear to you, I'd do it.
>> You cannot really trust
anybody's promises out here.
I don't know Debbie that well.
I've known her for ten days.
I don't know her personal
relationship with God or what
her swears to God mean, but,
you know, it's a very lucrative
offer.
A lock for sure on the final
two.
>> She just told Stephen and
myself that she would do
anything to see me and him
in the final two.
Those were her exact words.
>> Okay, she's out.
>> With Debbie making that
promise to Stephen and myself,
it also makes me wonder what
other promises she's made to
other people, uh, because she
shows she's willing to do
whatever it takes to move
forward in this game, even if
she says she only wants third
place.
Nobody wants third place in this
game.
>> Did she tell Taj the same
thing?
>> Yep, yep.
She goes.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Taj
returning from Exile Island.
>> Come on, Taj!
>> Hey!
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Coach.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to make your way through
a series of obstacles.
You'll dig your way under a log.
You'll go across a balance
beam, then under a rope crawl
and out into a field where you
will find ten spinning math
symbols.
You'll memorize the sequence of
symbols, then race back to your
answer board and write them
down in the same sequence to
solve a math equation.
First person to get all the
symbols right and the correct
answer to the equation wins
immunity and is guaranteed a
one-in-...
>> ALL: Five.
>> PROBST: Five shot at winning
the million bucks.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First stage is dig a big hole.
So you can crawl under.
Lost a lot of weight out here,
but you still want to make sure
you can get your butt through
that hole.
J.T. gonna give it a shot.
J.T. is stuck.
J.T. is halfway through.
Taj giving it a shot.
Taj is stuck.
J.T. is through!
J.T. moving through to the
crawl-through.
J.T. having a big lead right
now.
Memorize as many of those
symbols as you can in one shot.
Debbie's through the
crawl-through.
(mumbling)
Plus, plus.
>> PROBST: Stephen gonna have to
dig a lot more to squeeze
through.
J.T. across the beam.
Gotta get back through that
hole now before he can start
working on the answer.
Coach is now through.
He's heading out.
J.T. starting to work on his
answer.
Taj is through now.
Stephen squeaks through.
Stephen falls off.
J.T. heading out to try and
remember some more symbols.
Stephen falls off again.
Debbie back.
J.T.'s across again.
Stephen cannot get across the
balance beam.
He's quickly falling out of
this challenge.
Taj taking a look at the
symbols.
J.T. racing back.
Coach heading back.
Erinn is finally through!
Stephen finally across the
balance beam, but way behind.
Debbie heading back.
J.T. back from his second trip,
filling in the last of the
symbols.
J.T. working on the math portion
of this.
The symbols have to be right in
order for the math to be right.
Coach back with his first set
of symbols.
Stephen heading back after
being out there a long time.
Debbie back from her second
trip.
Taj back from her first trip.
Coach going to head out looking
for more symbols.
Debbie working on the math.
J.T. doing the math.
Stephen back with his first set
of symbols.
He was out there a long time.
How many can his brain hold?
Taj heading back out.
With only one look at the
symbols, Stephen's doing all of
this on one pass.
Is he right?
>> So, two minus...
>> PROBST: It's J.T. and Stephen
neck and neck.
>> Jeff, is that right?
>> PROBST: Stephen thinks he has
it.
>> I got it.
>> PROBST: If he did it, he did
it with only one look at the
symbols.
Stephen is right!
Stephen wins immunity!
>> Oh, my God!
I won immunity!
I can't even believe it!
(cheering)
>> PROBST: Stephen, I gotta ask
you.
You memorized all ten symbols in
one pass.
>> Well, I divided... I made
each symbol be a number so I had
plus is one, divided by is
four, times is three.
And I know the brain can
remember a seven-digit number
'cause that's why phone numbers
are seven digits.
So, I divided it into two
numbers, um, and just remembered
those two numbers.
>> PROBST: Well, it worked.
Come on over.
>> All right, Stephen!
>> PROBST: That was one of the
biggest come-from-behind
victories ever.
>> I was pretty much last.
>> PROBST: With this around his
neck, Stephen is safe at
tonight's Tribal Council.
J.T., Debbie, Coach, Taj, Erinn,
after 33 days out here, one of
you going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Nice work.
>> Thanks a lot, Jeff.
>> I look over at Stephen and I
see the necklace around his
neck, and it was just like I got
the necklace.
You know, every time something
goes our way, I try hard not to
do it, but I always look at
Stephen and smile because he
knows just like I do we just
keep battling it out.
Keep doing what we're doing.
We can do this.
>> Good job, Steve-o!
>> Thank you.
>> Steve-o.
Steve-o!
>> The day I did not think would
come.
>> I'm going to go and rinse
off.
>> Me, too.
>> Yeah.
>> Let me get some of this sand
off.
J.T. and I, we came into this
merge basically expecting to be
picked off.
And now we're in the dominant
position.
Now the Timbira people are
individually coming to us and,
you know, begging for our mercy.
So to have done that together
with Taj and J.T., to have
stuck tight, even when all of
these different factions were
vying for our attentions,
we feel pretty good about it.
>> Debbie thinks Coach...
>> Debbie is strategical woman
of the year.
>> Oh, my God.
She's sucking up to everybody.
>> She promised us if we'd take
her to the final three, she
would give up immunity and take
third place.
>> Get out.
>> Which we don't believe.
>> In the same day, she said
we've got to get rid of Erinn.
>> Get out.
>> So, I said, "Erinn, when
you got nauseous at the end,
Debbie just threw you under the
bus."
She said, "Coach, then you, and
then Taj, of course, next."
>> Oh, Lord.
He's like, "Are you okay out
here?"
I was like, "I have two brothers
that are taking care of me."
>> Taj really trusts Stephen
and myself.
I mean, we're her only two
guys out here.
It's good to know, you know,
that she's still sticking with
us, but no one else in this
entire tribe knows what's really
going on like Stephen and I do.
>> Huh?
The more you think about it?
>> The Debbie thing is not a
good idea.
What do you think?
The downsides of losing Debbie
are she is a really hard worker
around camp.
She is a very strong positive
presence.
I actually think she would step
aside at three and let J.T. and
me have it.
>> Man, that spa was so nice
right now.
>> We went at the wrong time.
We went when it was overcast and
gross.
>> Yeah.
>> You feeling good?
>> I'm feeling good now.
>> My ass.
(laughing)
>> Other downsides to losing
Debbie are a couple more days
here with Coach.
>> I think about it, and I've
got my instincts saying you've
got to get rid of Taj next
because if she has the idol,
she's going to play the five.
>> We're solid, man, the four
of us.
We don't have nothing to worry
about.
The only thing to get in our
way is the idol.
We play this right, that's over
with.
That's done.
Coach, you know, he's always
wanting to reassure that things
are going his way, and it's
just hard to deal with him.
I mean, I don't want to lie to
him.
>> All the way, fellas.
>> Let's do it.
>> Do you guys realize...
I'm just going to tell you this
right now.
I'm just going to throw a
reality check on you.
One of us three is going to win
it.
>> I hate lying to anybody, so
anybody I got to lie to, I try
to avoid them.
So the sooner I get the people
I've got to lie to out of the
game, the better.
>> Whether or not Debbie is
scheming, whether or not Coach
is delusional, right now it
doesn't matter.
We need to figure each move
strategically to make things
easier for the next move.
We don't need any of them to be
loyal right now; as long as we
have a strong alliance, we can
pick them off one by one.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Brendan, Tyson, and Sierra,
voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
Coach, from the beginning of
this game, you've talked about
going to the end with the best
players.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: With only six people
left, everybody can't be
equally deserving.
>> I think that, you know, what
might be considered a strength
in my mind might not be a
strength in somebody else's
mind.
Stephen, you know, he's a
warrior to me because he has
gone from a boy who likes to
read books about adventure to a
man who is living an adventure
and excelling at it without any
complaints.
>> PROBST: Let's go a little
further with this.
How about Debbie?
Why should she be here at the
end and not someone else
sitting up here?
>> I'd say that Debbie is
playing the game for the same
reasons that I am, and that is
for integrity.
And so that's why we paired up
on day three because I know she
will never lie to me,
no matter what.
>> PROBST: And because you feel
that way, that makes her the
best to go to the end.
>> I trust her implicitly.
She will not lie to me in this
game.
>> PROBST: Taj, how risky is
that for Coach to say, "I
paired up with Debbie on day
three?"
>> Um, it's not risky.
That's what people do.
You build alliances.
You do what you have to do to
survive in the game, and he's
done a great job.
He's a warrior.
He's a dragonslayer.
He-He's...
>> PROBST: A warrior.
>> That's what he says.
He's a warrior...
>> PROBST: That's what you said.
>> Because that's what he calls
himself.
>> I didn't come up with that,
by the way.
>> PROBST: Let me guess: some
chief in a small village...
(laughter)
>> That's fine.
Hey, every time we come in here
and you want to try to cut me
down because you want to try to
ferret out the truth, I love it.
>> PROBST: Okay.
Let's take it to the next step.
Tell me about Taj.
What is it that makes her best
to go to the end?
>> When I saw the raw emotions
of her the other day at the
auction, you know, she has made
the ultimate sacrifice, taking
time away from her son that
she'll never get back.
And so, that is incredible.
>> PROBST: Coach, how hard
would it be to vote out Taj
tonight after making that
sacrifice so that you guys
could all get your loved ones?
>> I think every time that each
one of us sit here and analyze
each person up here, we all
think, "Is it justifiable?"
And obviously, coming on the
heels of her doing something
like that, it would be very
difficult for any of us to
want to vote her out tonight.
>> PROBST: Now, let's turn the
tables.
J.T., what makes Coach worthy?
He talks about wanting to take
the best to the end.
What if he's not one of the
best?
>> Anyone that will stand here
and put himself out on the line
and be this honest, you know,
has never told a lie, deserves
to go as far as his body can
stand.
>> Debbie, what is working
against Coach making it to the
end?
>> I think Coach is determined
to be honest.
And this is a game that honesty
is huge, but can it really last
through the duration of this
game?
I don't know.
But if there is an Achilles'
heel on Coach, that could be it.
>> PROBST: Erinn, is tonight's
vote going to surprise somebody?
>> Um, there might be surprises
tonight.
>> PROBST: Debbie, how will
tonight's vote change this game?
>> Um, that's a really good
question, Jeff.
I think that it's going to
change the way this tribe
behaves and how we're going to
figure out who belongs where,
and, um, I do think it will be a
surprise.
>> PROBST: Stephen, you have
the individual immunity
necklace.
As always, it's yours to assign
to somebody else if you want
or keep it for yourself.
>> I'm going to hold on to it,
Jeff.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote
for Stephen.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Coach, you're up.
>> Taj, you're a beautiful soul.
Best of luck.
>> I'm sorry, Coach, but this
game is changing, and you wanted
to play it with honesty and
integrity, and it's time for you
to go.
Hope you forgive me.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Taj.
Coach.
One vote Taj; one vote Coach.
Debbie.
One vote Taj; one vote Coach;
one vote Debbie.
Debbie.
That's two votes Debbie;
one vote Taj; one vote Coach.
11th person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury:
Debbie.
That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Debbie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, there's no doubt the best
players will make it to the end.
The more interesting question:
of the five of you, who's the
best of the best?
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Erinn can't really control
what she says.
>> PROBST: Erinn loses ground
with her new alliance.
>> I just thought it was,
like, so tasteless.
>> I would hate for anything
that I said to send me home
before Coach.
>> Dragonslayer makes the
dragon cane.
>> PROBST: And Coach digs deep
to stay in the game.
>> Hit me with your best shot,
Pat Benatar.
(yelling)
>> I'm really the girly-girl,
and eating live fish and
sleeping in the freezing cold,
and just everything that I've
endured-- I am so proud of
myself.
And I know that it was a hard
decision for them to make to
vote me off tonight.
I don't hold any grudges.
This is a game and you got to
play it the best.
I'm anxious to sit on the jury
and see what goes down.