>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
In the highlands of Brazil...
>> Pow! (grunting)
>> PROBST: ...two tough tribes,
Jalapao and Timbira, battled it
out.
The winning tribe at each
reward challenge got to send
someone from the losing tribe
to Exile Island.
>> PROBST: But in a new twist...
Brendan, choose one member of
the winning tribe to join you
at Exile Island.
>> PROBST: This gave the Exiles
an opportunity to form a
cross-tribal alliance.
>> We got another clue.
>> We got another clue!
(laughing)
>> Perfect!
>> PROBST: Which they did,
sharing clues to immunity idols
hidden at each of their camps.
>> PROBST: They made plans to
strengthen their alliance by
bringing in Brendan's tribemate,
Sierra, and Taj's tribemate,
Stephen.
>> Do you want to be a part of
the biggest upset on Survivor
history?
>> Yes, I do.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: But Brendan never had
a chance to inform Sierra,
leaving Taj to do it the next
time at Exile Island.
>> Once we get to the merge,
we'll have a four-way alliance
that no one knows about and
can't break up.
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: Taj zeroed in on the
whereabouts of the hidden
immunity idol at Jalapao.
>> It's back at my home camp at
tree mail.
>> PROBST: But she didn't have a
chance to look for it.
However...
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Brendan made the
discovery at Timbira.
At the last immunity
challenge...
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Timbira does win
immunity!
Timbira evened things up when
they forced Jalapao to lose
another member.
Sandy, the tribe has spoken.
With the tribes dead even at
six apiece, it's anyone's game.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(Taj moaning)
>> Just...
(grunting)
Yes, right there!
Yes, yes!
Itchy, ooh!
Ahh, yes!
Oh, my God.
You're doing it, baby.
You are doing it.
We got rid of Sandy last night.
I only wrote Joe's name down on
the paper at, uh, Tribal Council
because I didn't want to put
Sandy's name down.
I need to get some more water.
I'm out of water.
>> I'll go with you.
>> Yeah, we can go fill up the
bottles together.
>> Right now, everything with
Brendan, Sierra, and Stephen is
in place.
We have the Exile Island
alliance intact.
Our main focus right now is to
find the idol.
We're just set with the four
people in place.
Now, all we need is the extra
ammunition and then it's on.
Something has to be...
Something must be something.
'Cause it says, "Why the sad
frown?"
>> That's what it is: "Why the
sad frown?"
>> That was the last clue.
"You get your mail from it
every day," and, uh, something
"round, and you'll ask it why
the sad frown."
>> I swear to you... Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God!
I found the immunity idol,
and I felt a very huge sense of
relief because everything is
complete now.
We have the foursome in place.
We have both the idols in place.
All we have to do now is make
it to the merge with everybody
intact.
"If you intend to use the
idol, you must reveal it or
give it away to someone else...
the votes have been cast... "
All right.
I just love it when a perfect
plan comes together.
It's so much fun!
(laughing)
Okay, stuff this in your pocket.
Do something with it.
Hide it.
>> Should we bury it or do you
think I should put it in my
pants?
>> Um, I think we should
keep it.
They won't suspect you.
They're looking at me.
>> Right.
>> So, keep it on you.
Keep it on you close.
Um, you know, if you bend down,
be cognizant that something will
show, the shape of your pockets
will show, so always protect
yourself.
Grab the bottle.
Let's get back.
>> Taj and I found the idol
together and she immediately
handed it off to me because
I was the one with pockets so I
could better conceal it.
>> Ooh, I'm sweating.
>> Oh, my God!
We got it, girl!
>> I know, I know, I told you
it was going to work out.
I'm telling you, once we make
it to the merge, it's smooth
sailing.
>> I mean, I'm delighted to
have it but, you know, as long
as it's in my possession, I'm
going to try to keep it in my
possession.
Theoretically and ostensibly,
it is mine.
I'm the one wearing the idol
around my neck.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
>> Ready to get cranking?
>> Yeah, want me to put the
beans on, get a fire going?
>> Yeah.
I gotta go down to the river
and wash pots and get water and
all that good stuff, so...
>> Yeah, might as well get
going.
>> Okay.
>> Are you coming, Brendan?
>> He's working on the fire.
>> Yeah, I'm going to get the
fire going.
>> Hey, Deb!
Who's all down there?
>> Coach and Tyson.
>> Okay, I wanted to know if
you need any extra hands.
>> We got it, I think.
Thanks. You rest.
>> Okay.
>> So...
>> Dude, you didn't tell me.
I was standing there and I walk
in and she's like, "I gotta
tell you about this four-way
alliance."
And I was like...
(laughing)
I'm gonna kill you.
>> Dude, but it works.
All right, so...
>> Were you going to tell me?
You bastard.
>> Yes!
I didn't have a chance to speak
with Sierra before the
challenge, so, I didn't tell her
about the plan with Taj.
It could have been disaster.
It could have blown the whole
thing up.
>> And then she got the clue.
>> Yeah.
>> She turned around to me and
she showed it to me.
>> Yep.
Yep, I have it.
>> Every single kind of stage
that we've set has worked and
every time we've layered more
people into the plan, you know,
we've gotten more and more
powerful.
Good, right?
>> That four-way alliance is
insane.
>> Perfect.
>> We're going down to the end
no matter what.
>> Yeah, perfect.
Uh-huh.
>> It's over.
Hallelujah, praise the Lord.
Amen, Jesus!
After three days of being a
loser when I first got here,
I'm proud of myself.
I formed an amazing alliance.
It's really quite brilliant.
We're going to take over the
whole world.
That's right.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Timbira getting your first look
at the new Jalapao tribe.
Sandy voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> Only a matter of time.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Today's challenge
will be played in rounds.
Each round, one tribe member
will be seated on a spinning
platform.
On my "go," another tribe
member will race while pulling
a rope attached to that
platform, causing the tribe
member to get dizzy.
The dizzy tribe member must
then make their way across the
balance beam to the finish line.
Each time you win a round for
your tribe, you score a point.
First tribe to three points
wins a reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: For today's reward,
you will be taken to the Charmin
Café...
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: ...where you will
enjoy some nice, strong coffee,
pastries.
You'll also have a modern toilet
and plenty of Charmin.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will choose one
member of the losing tribe to
go to Exile.
That person will select
somebody from the winning tribe
to join them, which means one
person from the winning tribe
will not enjoy the Charmin Café.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Big stakes.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize.
Then we'll get started.
Here we go.
First round, for Jalapao, Joe
will be pulling Taj.
For Timbira, Brendan will be
pulling Tyson.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Joe!
>> Joe, you got this, Joe.
>> PROBST: Here they go!
Taj getting a spin.
Tyson getting a spin.
>> Come on, Brendan!
>> You got it, Joe.
You got it, Joe!
>> Hold on, Tyson, hold on.
>> PROBST: Joe and Brendan very
even.
Gotta get up and off while
you're dizzy.
>> Whoo, whoo!
>> PROBST: Taj giving it a go.
>> Whoa!
>> Come on, Taj!
Come on, Taj!
>> Taj, come on!
>> I'm coming!
>> Hey, relax, Taj, relax.
>> Come on, Tyson.
Come on, baby.
>> PROBST: Tyson taking his
time.
If you fall off, you have to go
back.
>> Slow down, Taj, slow down,
Taj, slow down.
>> Oh, come on, Taj!
>> She's back at the start,
Tyson.
Take your time.
>> Hurry, hurry, hurry!
>> PROBST: We are neck and neck.
Tyson and Taj, both very close.
Tyson's across.
>> Yeah, baby!
Yeah, baby!
>> PROBST: Tyson wins for
Timbira!
Timbira up 1-zip.
Playing to three.
Next round, Stephen will be
pulling Spencer.
Coach will be pulling Erinn.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> You got this, boy!
>> Go, Stephen!
>> Get it down there!
>> PROBST: Coach pulling Erinn.
Erinn really spinning.
Stephen pulling Spencer.
>> Oh!
>> Go, Erinn!
Erinn, off, off!
>> Go, Stephen, go, go!
Here we go.
>> Take your time, Erinn, take
your time.
>> Breathe, breathe.
>> Take your time.
>> Take a second.
>> Let it get off you.
Let it get off you.
>> That's a boy, Spence.
>> Yeah, Spence!
Keep going, baby!
>> Take your time, Erinn, take
your time.
>> He's off! He's off!
>> PROBST: Erinn with a big lead
if she can hang on.
She doesn't.
>> She's off.
>> Come on, Spencer!
>> PROBST: Spencer now with a
shot.
>> Come on, Spence!
>> Look at those steady little
legs!
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: Spencer's across!
>> PROBST: Jalapao wins!
Jalapao evens it up, 1-1.
>> That was like beer goggles,
man.
>> PROBST: Next round, Joe will
be spinning J.T.
Brendan will be spinning Sierra.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Joe and Brendan dead even.
Big sprints.
>> Hold on, Sierra.
Hold on.
>> Atta boy, Joe.
>> PROBST: J.T. spinning.
Sierra is flying.
>> Hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on.
>> You got it, Joe.
You got it, Joe.
>> Good job.
>> Sierra!
>> Breathe, breathe, breathe.
Breathe.
You're okay. You're okay.
>> Focus, J.!
>> PROBST: J.T. trying to get
rid of that dizziness.
Like the end of a bad Friday
night for J.T.
Sierra struggling with the
dizziness.
Take your time, girl.
>> You got it, J.T.
Give it a go, J.T.
Give it a go.
>> Come on, girl.
You got this.
>> Take your time, Sierra.
>> PROBST: J.T. falls off
quickly, Sierra with the early
lead.
>> He's way back.
Take your time.
>> He's not even on it.
>> Relax, J.T., relax.
Use your arms to balance.
>> PROBST: She can't hang on.
Sierra's off.
J.T. nearly across.
J.T. is across.
Jalapao wins round three.
Jalapao leads 2-1.
Playing to three.
Next round, Stephen pulling
Sydney.
Coach pulling Debra.
Timbira, got to win this round
to stay alive.
Jalapao wins, you win reward.
Survivors ready?
Go.
>> Let's go, Stephen!
>> PROBST: This is it, Timbira's
last chance.
>> Coach, you got this!
>> Go, Steve-o, go, Steve-o, go!
>> Atta boy, Steve-o!
>> Come on!
Stephen, you're beating him,
baby!
>> Atta boy, Stephen!
Come on!
>> PROBST: This is it.
Both women are free.
>> Come on, Syd.
>> Take a breather.
>> Come you, you little
ballerina.
>> PROBST: Debbie up on the
balance beam first.
>> Come on, Debbie!
>> PROBST: Sydney making quick
work of the first half of the
balance beam.
>> Come on, Syd.
>> PROBST: Sydney almost, but
not enough.
Debbie can tie things up for
Timbira if she hangs on.
Sydney hustling to catch Debbie.
>> Hurry, Deb.
>> Go, Deb!
>> You got this, Sydney.
>> Come on, Syd.
>> Go, go go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Sydney is across!
Jalapao wins reward at The
Charmin Café.
Jalapao, congratulations.
Nice afternoon awaiting you
guys.
Let's get down to the business
at hand.
Who are you going to choose
from Timbira to go to Exile
Island?
>> We're going to send Brendan
again.
>> Brendan going back to Exile
Island for Timbira.
You're smiling.
>> It's evil to be able to pick
somebody that just won a reward
and take them out of it.
>> PROBST: All right, Brendan,
who are you choosing from
Jalapao to go with you?
>> Stephen.
>> What?
>> I love you.
>> Oh...
>> Brendan, that was a classy
move, man.
That was classy, dude.
>> I don't know what's going on
in Brendan's head, but, uh, he's
made a lot of contact with the
other tribe.
Whether he's built up
friendships or alliances,
I don't know.
But, uh, he definitely seems to
have some of their respect, and
it could get dangerous.
>> PROBST: Jalapao,
congratulations.
Grab your stuff.
Head out.
>> Enjoy.
Have some for us.
>> PROBST: You guys have a fun
afternoon in store.
The Charmin Café is waiting.
>> The Charmin Café.
>> Charmin.
>> Yay!
>> I like Charmin.
>> That's awesome.
>> Aww.
>> Oh, my God!
>> We can lay down after we eat.
>> What are these?
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God, y'all.
>> Who wants one of these?
>> I want one of everything.
>> I want everything.
>> This is so good.
>> I was very excited to go on a
reward because every time we
win the reward challenge, I end
up going to Exile, every time.
I'm going to eat until I hurt.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> All that food.
All the coffee and the juice
and the fresh water.
I didn't know what to do.
I forgot my name.
I was just going crazy.
I was so happy.
>> Look over there.
>> A potty!
>> With soap.
There's soap over there!
>> I'll take this over fishing
gear any day.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> It's cool getting to know my
tribe because every time you
go to Exile, you just separate
yourself from the tribe.
But I'm not really worried
about that because there's a
whole 'nother story going on
with the secret alliance that no
one even knows about.
So, since I do have a plan B,
I don't feel so nervous.
You spun me around like a damn
tornado.
>> I think Taj being gone all
this time really hurts her.
All the rest of us, we've been
able to really kind of gain
some trust with each other, and
even talk strategy, and she
hasn't had the opportunity to
create a tighter bond.
>> Hey, you guys!
>> What's over there?
>> Oh, cool!
What is it?
>> What is it?
>> I don't know what it is.
>> Is that a menu?
>> Maybe it's a gift
certificate.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God.
What is this?
>> No way, dude.
>> Oh, it is a letter.
Oh, my God!
>> From my family.
>> Oh!
>> Yeah!
>> No way!
(squeals)
>> I'm so happy!
>> No way!
"Everybody misses you like
crazy."
>> My mom would write two pages.
>> J.T. found letters from home,
and it was not something that we
expected.
And it was definitely the most
important reward we've had so
far, as far as just for mental
strength.
>> Aw...
>> To have that reminder that,
hey, your family is at home
waiting for you.
There is something outside the
game.
>> Oh, man.
>> All my nieces gave me
something.
>> Oh, this is good, man.
(crying)
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> I know, y'all.
>> Sorry.
>> Tears of joy.
It's the first time my dad's
ever said something like,
"Be careful and be safe."
>> She said it there?
>> She told me at the end.
I almost started crying.
>> Yeah, I almost lost it there
for...
>> Oh, God.
Being out here for so long, you
almost forget what home is like
and what the people are like
that you love and to get a
letter, and to just hear them
tell you that they miss you and
they're proud of you and they
just...
Oh!
That was just the icing on the
cake.
I would have been sick if I had
to go to Exile and miss that.
>> This is not much for us to
eat, you know.
>> Out of all the challenges so
far, I wanted that one the most.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yeah.
Brendan right now, the way he's
going to Exile, and the people
that he's choosing for Exile,
is making strong allies.
If we merge, he has control of
the game, and I'm a bystander.
And I certainly don't want that
to happen.
Feel the breeze shift?
I've noticed that the wind
blows this way predominantly.
But when there's a storm
coming, it switches directions.
It turns this way.
But it doesn't look too crazy
because it looks like the
clouds are breaking up on the
horizon.
(thunder rumbles)
>> Oh, my gosh.
Coach is kind of a jackass.
He's been running his mouth
about the weather at camp.
I think Coach really, truly
wants to be this, like,
"Survivor Man."
I would not be surprised if,
when this game is all said and
done, Coach said, "Gotcha!
I'm an accountant.
I've never left Nebraska."
>> So, uh, this is your
Brazilian hideaway?
>> This is my vacation pad.
>> It's-it's quite stunning.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, cool.
So this will be fun.
>> Yeah.
>> Awesome.
Awesome, awesome, awesome.
I picked Stephen to go to Exile
in order to put the final piece
of the puzzle in place.
He didn't know me, didn't know
Sierra, so I'm really excited
to catch up with him about,
you know, how we could work
together, just to make him feel
comfortable with that alliance.
So this is the view from the
top.
>> Oh, man.
Oh, wow.
>> It's pretty, right?
>> It is.
>> It's crazy.
It's like an oasis.
>> We've got the hidden immunity
idol.
>> You brought it with you?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, nice.
You guys actually have it.
>> Yeah.
>> I was concerned she didn't
have it.
>> No. We got it this morning.
>> You did?
>> Yeah.
>> When Stephen and I first
arrived, we started talking
immediately, and he told me that
he had the hidden immunity idol.
I told him I had also had found
the idol, so now this
four-person alliance has both
immunity idols, which is great
because it's going to put us in
a powerful spot.
>> Yeah.
So, there's more wood.
We should probably just go grab
more big trunks like that and
load up for tonight.
>> Cool.
Brendan.
My first impression of him is
positive, but wary.
He's obviously an extremely
strong player.
He's mentally strong and he's
clearly strategically strong.
But, you know, it's hard to
trust someone who...
You know, I've known him for
five minutes.
I can't place my entire faith in
the game on him.
So, I might keep this two-tribe
alliance in the back of my head
as something that might be
there, but I can't place my
entire faith on this
four-person alliance.
>> I had a crazy dream last
night.
>> About what?
>> My boyfriend, Kelly.
He had, like, a salsa...
a, like, chips and salsa thing
in his hand as this earthquake
was going on.
It was just really strange.
But it was nice to see Kelly.
>> Right.
>> I woke up.
I'm like, "I have to marry this
guy."
I can't live without this guy."
So, no girls to whet your
appetite?
No one does it for you?
>> None, uh...
None right now.
There are a lot of cute girls at
U.F., though.
>> Yeah?
>> A lot of them, yeah.
I'm not in a rush.
There's, there are those people
who just need to be in a
relationship.
They just need to have that
person.
I'm like, I'm not one of those
people.
>> Yeah.
>> So I don't know.
>> It's nice to be free.
>> Yeah.
>> Especially at your age.
>> Feel like that's pretty cool.
My tribe mates are not aware
that I'm gay.
I haven't told them, only
because I feel like, in the
culture that we live in,
there's nothing really to gain,
or not much to gain, by people
finding out that you are gay.
I figure, I've got time in the
future.
I'm not getting married anytime
soon.
>> Gosh, all you have is time.
>> I know, so...
I don't like hiding it, though.
I would like to be able to have
those conversations.
When we're talking about girls,
I-I wouldn't mind, you know,
making like, "Spencer, what type
of guy do you like?" or
something.
But I know that that's not the
best option for me in the game
at this point, so...
>> Tree mail!
"Connecting with your tribe
will keep you alive.
Battling the others is part of
the game.
The meek and the slow will lose
one more.
The aggressive protect their
flame."
>> "Connecting with your tribe."
>> Guys like J.T., typical
Southerners, you know, people
who are generally not quite as
accepting of homosexuality, and
I don't know if he's one of
those guys, but they are maybe
inclined to get rid of somebody
like me just based on fact that
I am gay.
>> This is definitely my kind
of game right here.
I can catch and throw anything.
>> And that's disappointing.
And it's one of the reasons why
I keep it a secret.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Brendan and
Stephen, returning from Exile
Island.
>> Welcome back.
>> What's up, Stevie?
>> Hello.
>> Oh.
You need some water?
>> Awesome.
>> PROBST: Guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things
first; Debbie, give it up.
>> I missed you guys.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, two
members of each tribe will
alternate launching balls out
onto the course, where the
remaining tribe members will
catch the ball.
It doesn't matter what color
the ball is.
You catch a ball from either
tribe, you score a point for
your tribe.
First tribe to five wins
immunity.
Losing tribe, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be voted out
of this game.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, give you
a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
The launchers for Jalapao:
Sydney and Stephen.
For Timbira: Erinn and Debbie.
Guarding each other:
Brendan and Taj;
Coach and Joe;
Spencer and Tyson;
Sierra and J.T.
It's first to five.
Survivors ready?
Three, two, one, launch!
Erinn goes short over to
Brendan, who just misses.
>> J.T.!
>> PROBST: Sydney goes deep to
J.T.
J.T. with a great snag for
Jalapao!
>> J.T.!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Jalapao on the board
with their first point.
Okay, here we go.
Next round.
Three, two, one, launch.
Debbie goes deep.
Stephen goes deep.
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: J.T. with another
great catch!
Joe!
>> In his hand.
>> PROBST: In and out, in and
out.
Does not count.
Got to catch it in the net.
J.T. snags one for Jalapao.
We are now at 2-zip.
>> Oh, boy.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Three, two, one, launch.
Erinn and Sydney both release
their balls.
Brendan with a nice stab.
J.T. just misses.
Timbira on the board now with
their first point.
>> All right, Brendan!
>> PROBST: Jalapao leads 2-1.
>> Let's go, guys.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
launch.
Both balls in the air.
Brendan with a great snag for
Timbira.
We are now at 2-2.
>> Taj, come on, baby.
>> Hey, I am doing my best.
>> PROBST: Taj is wearing down.
That's giving Brendan a big
opening.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, launch.
Both balls in the air.
J.T. snags another one for
Jalapao!
>> Oh, he knocked a tooth.
>> We've got a tooth out.
>> He just lost a tooth.
>> PROBST: Ah.
J.T. has lost a tooth.
>> J.T.!
>> PROBST: Wait, J.T., did you
just throw it?
>> PROBST: Let's find the tooth.
Let's find the tooth.
You're going to want that tooth.
>> It's only half of it.
>> I-I didn't see him get hit.
>> Is that it?
You want this back, J.T.?
>> No, it-it don't matter.
>> PROBST: Here, I'll hold it.
Give it to me.
(Taj groans)
>> Oh, my God.
(Sydney exhales sharply)
>> Are you bleeding, J.T.?
You all right, man?
>> PROBST: For the first time
ever in the history of
Survivor, a point was scored
while losing a tooth.
We are now at 3-2.
Jalapao leads.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, launch.
Both balls in the air.
Tyson almost snags it for
Timbira.
>> Yeah, J.T.!
>> PROBST: J.T., unbelievable!
Another catch for Jalapao!
>> Yeah, J.T.!
>> PROBST: We are now at 4-2.
Jalapao needs just one more
point to win.
>> Yeah!
We got this.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
launch.
>> Get it, Spencer!
>> Come on, Spence!
>> PROBST: Tyson, nice grab for
Timbira.
>> Tyson!
>> Come on, Spence.
>> PROBST: Tyson keeps Timbira
alive.
>> Yeah, Tyson!
>> PROBST: Jalapao leads 4-3.
>> Let it go, Spence.
Let's do this.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
launch.
Debbie short, Stephen long.
>> Get it, Spence!
>> PROBST: Tyson right there!
Tyson snags another one for
Timbira!
>> Let's go, Tyson.
>> PROBST: Jalapao's lead has
evaporated.
We're now tied 4-4, playing to
five.
Whoever scores the next point
wins immunity.
>> They want them shorter, yeah.
>> Here we go, guys.
Here we go, guys.
>> PROBST: Three...
>> Short, short!
>> PROBST: ...two, one, launch.
Erinn goes short.
Sydney goes deep.
Tyson scores for Timbira!
J.T. just misses for Jalapao.
Timbira wins immunity!
(women shrieking)
(J.T. grunts)
>> Good job, guys.
>> Good job.
>> My man!
Mwah!
>> PROBST: Timbira,
congratulations, immunity again.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: No Tribal Council,
nobody going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back camp.
Have a good night.
>> Good job, y'all.
>> Great job, J.T.
>> PROBST: J.T., amazing effort,
almost single-handedly won that
challenge for Jalapao.
Instead, you came up short.
The only thing I have for you
is your tooth.
Tribal Council tonight, Jalapao.
Somebody going home.
You have the afternoon to
figure out who it's going to be.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you at Tribal.
>> I'm doing everything I can
to win.
Broke the back half of my front
tooth off, but it just seemed
like some people wasn't giving
it all.
I don't want to get rid of
anyone, but it's got to be
Spencer.
(birds chirping)
>> I was hot today.
I was so hot, I was exhausted.
And I was hot meaning angry.
Today's challenge frustrated me
to no end.
I just, I'm telling you, I just
really felt like it was brutal.
>> No, it's already scabbed up
a little bit.
>> Oh, yeah, it is swollen up
around it.
>> Yeah.
>> Joe and J.T. got beat up bad.
And I was angry because I fell
short today.
I think I'm a target, but I
completely believe that they're
crazy to keep Spencer over me
if they're trying to keep the
tribe strong because I think,
uh, Spencer, his play today was
far worse than anybody else's.
We're only down one.
I think whatever we need to do
next needs to be the best
chance to make it even, 5-5 at
the merge.
That means everybody needs to
leave their little emotions out
of it and think for the team.
Everybody.
You, him, everybody.
I'm-I'm hot today.
So I don't give a ... what
nobody thinks about me today.
Everybody can kiss my ass.
>> Can we talk through this
thing?
>> We can talk, but I just
want it to be...
I'm not going to sit here and
talk bull.
talk stuff, and then we do
something different at Tribal
Council.
Do what's going to be best for
the team.
>> If it makes you feel any
better, Taj, I trust you more
than I do other people in the
tribe.
>> Well, thank you.
>> Me, too.
>> I trust you, for sure.
>> You trust me?
>> I trust everybody here.
>> Why haven't you never come to
me for an-an ally?
Why have you never come to me
like that?
No, you've never come to me like
that.
You've never said to me and
said, "Let's do this together"
or "Let's try to..."
You've never...
>> It's a two-way road, right?
>> Hey, I've tried to talk to
you.
I'm not attacking you.
I'm just pissed today, and I'm
sick of this game, sick of it.
>> Taj was-was hot at me.
I-I really don't know why.
She can bat every eyelash and
raise every feather that she
has, but, you know, I think
moves like that out here will
get you voted off, bottom line.
And if Taj has the idol, I
think it's the best decision.
>> I think she's just scared.
I mean, you know, at least...
she has an emotional outburst,
but it's totally honest.
What do you think?
>> I have a really tough choice
ahead tonight because,
theoretically, I am better
served by Taj going home
without the idol because that
means it's mine to keep,
but right now, Taj, she's my
real connection with the
Timbira side of the Exile
alliance, Brendan and Sierra.
So I'm not totally clear what
I'm going to do.
>> I'm just pissed off, man.
I'm so pissed off.
I feel like we just let that
one go.
It could very well possibly be
it for me tonight, but I still
have the immunity idol.
And I have Steve kind of
keeping an ear out for
everything that's going on.
He'll let me know if I really
need to pull it out or not.
They're down there
whispering, so if you all want
to get a piece, go ahead.
>> Today's challenge was very
frustrating because I'm a
competitive person.
And I hate not only to lose,
but also to perform badly.
And I knew that J.T.
was probably going to be
frustrated with me.
>> I don't have any problem
writing his name down because
Spencer try and guess where it
was going.
That was obvious.
He's not going to listen to
what you tell him.
He's going to do it his way.
He wants everybody to do it
his way.
His way... you know.
Whatever.
I just want to win, man.
>> We have to win now.
>> Yeah, I hate losing.
>> It's rough around camp.
It's very, very tense.
And it's scary for sure
because things switch so
quickly in this game.
>> What do you think, Spencer?
>> I figured you'd come back
pissed at me, so...
>> I was pissed at you,
especially the challenge.
>> You think I wasn't giving my
effort?
>> It didn't look like you
tackled him.
I said, "Tackle him."
>> I knew I was probably going
to be on the chopping block,
so...
>> I can't speak for the whole
team.
I'm just telling you how I
feel, you know.
>> I know, but, obviously, you
have pull in the tribe, and...
I feel like it would be
beneficial to the tribe to keep
me for the next immunity
challenge.
I feel... obviously, I want to
stay, but I feel like I'm not
the worst person to keep around.
But that's...
obviously up to the other five
people who are voting, not just
me.
Who do you think should go?
>> I don't know.
>> You can tell me.
>> I think you or Taj.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's challenge.
Spencer, how did you feel about
your performance today?
>> My performance today was
pretty pathetic.
I definitely felt like I let my
guys down, and I was just very
upset with myself just the whole
time.
>> PROBST: Taj, do you feel
this tribe is still staying
together well or, after a loss,
can you feel the effect of
losing?
>> We can definitely feel the
the effect of losing.
And, of course, everybody's
frustrated, so we're just
trying to believe that the next
challenge we'll be able to tie
it up and go into the merge
even, at least.
>> PROBST: So how does that
manifest itself back at camp?
>> Well, initially, we all kind
of blew up.
Well, I won't say we all...
I kind of blew up because I
just felt like it was so
mismatched that... I don't know,
I just felt like we could have
definitely done a better job,
and I got upset.
>> PROBST: Joe, what does it
feel like to have somebody walk
up and start attacking you?
>> You don't ever like to walk
into a room and have fingers
pointed at you, especially when
it's not necessarily
even warranted.
>> PROBST: Taj, does it worry
you that you could have an
outburst that could cost you in
this game?
>> Anything you do could cost
you this game.
So an outburst is just another
form of anything that can
happen to get you out of this
game.
And at that point, I felt like I
was on my way out the door.
>> PROBST: And what made feel
that, your performance?
>> You know what, I don't know,
it's just a feeling you get that
your head is next.
And I was pissed off because,
at every challenge, I do give
110%, no matter if we lose or
win, and to even have the idea
that you're going to go out, and
I'm trying to figure out why.
I was hot.
So whoever was there was going
to get it, and I didn't care
who.
>> PROBST: Spencer, do you know
what she's talking about in
terms of just a gut: "People
aren't talking to me the same
way, or they're avoiding me."
>> Absolutely.
It definitely changes when you
get back to camp, and you know
that your head could be on the
chopping block.
Today, I had the same feeling
because of my performance in
the challenge and the
frustration with J.T.
during the challenge.
I came back knowing that I
could very well be going home
tonight.
It's not a feeling that is
enjoyable, for sure.
But I know what she's talking
about, and I definitely felt it
a bit today, too.
>> PROBST: Taj, you've spent a
lot of time out on Exile Island.
>> That I have.
>> PROBST: That can work two
ways: you're gone so much,
they don't have any reason to
get rid of you; you're gone so
much they don't know you, might
as well get rid of her.
>> Yeah, and, I mean, what can
I do about it?
I don't ask to go to Exile, so
it's not like I had a choice.
There's nothing I can do about
it except for fit in when I
come back.
>> PROBST: Do you feel the
target on your back, spending so
much time away from the tribe?
>> I didn't start feeling that
until maybe this week, just
because we're down to no more
expendable people.
I'm, like, that person, I
guess, if they thought I had
the idol, they didn't think I'd
need to be here because,
obviously, I would be a threat.
>> PROBST: Joe, how do you deal
with Taj, knowing she's been
out there three times, a lot of
opportunities to find the
hidden immunity idol.
>> You can't ever be certain.
She could definitely have it.
I haven't actually heard her
say the words, "I do not have
the immunity idol."
>> Would you like me to say it
now?
>> No, you don't have to.
>> Okay.
>> See, so stuff like that
makes you think that she's
really being aggressive about
hiding this thing or lying
about it if she does have it.
>> If I did say something,
would it mean I did had it.
>> No, I'm just saying, little
indicators like that,
>> I can't win.
>> So she hasn't slipped once,
so I believe her.
>> PROBST: And yet she still
has not said she doesn't have
it.
>> You want to say it for me?
>> I do not have the idol.
>> Okay, see, I believe her.
>> Should I say it to everyone
here?
>> I believe her.
>> PROBST: And that is what it
comes down to: whether or not
you believe what the people in
your tribe are telling you.
Somebody is about to find out
the truth.
It is time to vote.
Joe, you're up.
>> I'm pretty sure it's either
me or you tonight.
>> You played a hell of a game
and I'm sorry it came down to
this.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would the time to
do so.
All right, once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Spencer.
Taj.
One vote Spencer; one vote Taj.
Spencer.
Two votes Spencer; one vote Taj.
That's three votes Spencer;
one vote Taj.
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins: Spencer.
That's four votes.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Spencer, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Bye, guys.
>> PROBST: Well, you've lost two
immunity challenges in a row,
two tribe members in a row.
Worse than that, you lost
momentum.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> Ready? And...
>> You're solid, right?
>> PROBST: Join us next time.
>> To the strains...
>> PROBST: ...for a special
episode of Survivor: Tocantins.
>> ♪ Ba-ba-ba ♪
>> Who is this jackass?
>> Well, I just got voted out.
I lasted 15 days, but
definitely could have lasted a
lot longer.
I definitely made some friends
when I was out there and I hope
they feel the same way.
It's just frustrating that they
feel like I wasn't useful enough
in challenges.
It was just a really bad
challenge for me today, and I
feel like as far as my attitude
in tense situations.
I'm going to work on that.