>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor--
>> People who don't play this
game even half as bold as me,
pisses me off.
>> PROBST: Coach thought he was
in the driver's seat.
>> I think Taj has to go next.
>> PROBST: But Debbie turned on
her old ally.
>> It is not good for me to be
attached to Coach.
People are tired of him.
Okay, so he's going to think
we're voting off Taj.
I think we need to go ahead and
get Coach out, but it has to be
every single one of us writing
it down.
>> PROBST: So the Jalapao three
and Erinn decided Debbie was
too dangerous to keep around.
>> Yeah, she goes.
>> PROBST: Coach was clueless as
he watched his longtime ally go
home.
Debbie, the tribe has spoken.
Can Coach regain control?
Five are left, who will be
voted out tonight?
>> I'm in shock.
Tonight at Tribal, I thought I
was the one going home when I
saw my name.
And then it was Debbie, Debbie,
Debbie.
>> Coach.
>> Yes, sir?
>> What?
>> That's who wrote your name
down.
>> I can't grasp that.
I'm like... I'm like the lamb
led to the slaughterhouse around
here, that's what I feel like.
Oh, my goodness.
>> I was like, wow, J.T.,
Erinn and Taj and Stephen
mounted a counterattack
against Debbie to save me.
And it would have been very easy
to vote me out.
You know, I know I'm a
dangerous player in this game,
and so I'm-I'm just shocked.
Thanks for protecting me.
>> I mean, it was...
>> Holy cow!
So what's the lesson in this?
I think that the game is still
being played with truth.
I think the game is still being
played with honesty.
And I think this is the first
time in this game that I'm
almost speechless.
Almost.
>> Sorry to lay that one on
you before bed.
>> Yeah.
>> Now I just want to talk to
J.T. and Stephen and just ask
them when am I going?
Just tell me when I'm going.
Because obviously, Coach Wade's
no longer in control of this
game, and I don't know what's
going to happen next.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
>> My mind is blown.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah.
>> I've got a question before
I go off and cut down two...
>> Yeah.
>> I just want to be in
agreement with you guys on what
you want to do.
>> I know. Man, my lungs feel
like--
>> Are you all right?
You looked ruined yesterday.
>> I feel like I scarred my
lungs yesterday.
And my lungs feel like I smoked
20 cigars in a row yesterday and
inhaled all of them.
But, I mean, like, for me, it's
whatever you guys want.
I was talking to the guys about
Exile.
And I don't want to go to Exile.
Nobody wants to go to Exile at
this point.
I just hope my asthma doesn't
play up.
That's a horrible excuse.
You know, that's my only fear.
I'm just making it out here.
This asthma is kicking my ass.
My back is killing me every day.
So how do I handle that
adversity?
>> So what do you think, Coach?
>> You know what I think is
the-the noble thing is that we
send J.T. or myself.
But the cold, calculating
competitor in me wants to send
Taj or Erinn.
It's really up to you guys what
you think.
I just want to all be on the
same page.
>> Oh, God! I mean, J.T. and I
are eager to send Coach to
Exile.
He has been so skittish about
it.
He has been selling out
everyone trying to get them to
go to Exile before him.
I mean, you know, Coach has
mentioned ailments, you know, a
back problem, asthma, but it
never seemed to really affect
his performance.
So I'm not entirely sure Coach
can build a fire and cook this
food by himself.
I don't know.
I think he's scared.
Do you want to just tell him?
>> Huh?
>> You want to just tell him
we're sending him to Exile?
>> Doesn't matter.
Coach, he's just really scared
to go to Exile.
Such an adventurous soul as
Coach shouldn't really be scared
to go to Exile.
So I'm ready to test him, and
also we plan on sending
Coach home at the next Tribal
Council, so it would be nice
for him to come very weak to
the next immunity challenge.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
What's up, final five?
>> Hi.
>> How you doing, Jeff?
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's challenge
you will race through a maze.
You must then build a pole long
enough to retrieve a sandbag.
You'll swing the sandbag in an
attempt to knock over three
targets, raising a flag.
First person to raise their
flag wins.
One more element to this
challenge-- you will run the
entire challenge with your feet
shackled together.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: The winner of this
challenge will be taken on an
overnight reward.
You will leave camp.
You will be taken to the
governor's retreat, where you
will enjoy a bed, a shower, a
feast.
In addition, the winner will
send one person to Exile Island.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: I know it is.
We'll draw for spots, we'll get
started.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
J.T. in the lead.
Is he right?
Everybody following J.T.,
except Taj.
She's going her own way.
Somebody's going to be right,
somebody's going to be wrong.
Stephen hits a dead end.
>> This is dumb!
>> PROBST: Taj hits a dead end.
J.T.'s on the right course.
Coach right behind.
Coach taking the smart strategy.
He's just going to follow J.T.,
let him lead.
Erinn going to follow Coach and
J.T.
It's follow the leader.
J.T. and Coach through the
second section of the maze.
Erinn right in it.
Taj and Stephen falling out of
it.
J.T. having no trouble at all
with this maze.
Coach having no trouble
following him.
J.T. and Coach entering the
final section of the maze.
J.T. is through the maze.
Coach right behind.
Now you've got to start working
on that pole.
>> You guys, help me out here.
>> PROBST: Erinn, Stephen, Taj,
now very far behind.
Right now this challenge is
between J.T. and Coach.
>> Come on, J.T.
>> PROBST: Coach would love to
win a reward.
>> Damn right about that.
>> Back, back, back, back, back.
>> PROBST: J.T. already working
on his pole.
Coach still untying his pieces.
Taj through the maze.
Erinn through the maze.
Stephen through the maze.
Everybody's now working on
their pole.
J.T. has a nice pole coming
along.
Coach picking up the pace.
J.T. with a bit of a lead.
J.T. now has four pieces of
pole together.
Once you think your pole is
long enough, reach for that
sandbag.
J.T. has his pole together, and
has reached for his bag.
Coach needs to pick it up.
J.T. knocks over his first
target.
>> Nice job.
>> PROBST: There are a total of
three targets you have to hit.
J.T.'s knocked over his second
target.
One target left for a big
reward.
Coach now in on it.
Will his pole reach?
J.T. wins reward!
>> Whoo!
>> That was awesome.
>> All right!
(applause)
>> PROBST: J.T., come on over.
First order of business, sending
one person to Exile island.
They will not go on the reward.
They will not go back to camp.
They will have another hot,
probably wet stay away from all
of the politics of what is
going on these last few days.
Exile is the one place you do
not want to be on Day 34.
>> Any volunteers?
Let's be noble, Coach.
>> Okay.
>> Let's do this.
>> Yep.
>> Me and you's the only two
that hasn't been, man.
>> You bet.
>> Thank you, J.T.
>> PROBST: Coach, how do you
feel about going to Exile?
>> I'm good. I'm going to take
the monastic approach.
I'm not gonna build a fire,
not gonna eat.
I'm just gonna meditate.
>> He's going to take the martyr
approach, so when he comes back
he can not have eaten, not have
slept, not have had any water,
to-- minimizing the experiences
of some, I feel like-- and have
an excuse when he doesn't win
immunity when he gets back.
>> That's pretty harsh.
>> Kind of how I feel. Sorry.
>> PROBST: Is there something
to what Erinn said about maybe
trying to put yourself in the
position so that you've had the
worst experience at Exile?
>> I want it to be tough on me,
that's for sure.
I'm not going to minimize
everybody's experience.
In fact, I'm disappointed
that Erinn would say that.
You know, since the beginning
of the game she wanted to
try to, uh, cut me down a
little bit and a lot of
times when people do that it's
to vault themselves over.
I think maybe she wants to leave
here with the toughest Exile
experience.
And I don't want to take that
away from her.
As far as coming back and
winning immunity, my body is
about this close right now
from, uh, total disaster.
I've got, uh, disks on the right
side that have ruptured.
I feel my left one is about
ready to slip.
My asthma is choking me up so
bad I can't breathe.
There's no excuse about if I win
immunity or if I don't win
immunity.
I make no excuses.
So, you know, you can throw
stones at me, you can, everybody
else can and I go like this.
Give me your best shot.
Hit me with your best shot, Pat
Benatar, doesn't matter to me.
>> PROBST: All right, Coach,
grab your personal items.
Head out.
Coach will return in time for
the next immunity challenge.
>> I bit you guys adieu.
>> Thank you, Coach.
>> PROBST: All right, J.T.,
let's get to the reward.
You're going to take one person
with you, meaning you're going
to leave two people behind.
Maybe the best reward so far.
Who you taking with?
>> I gotta, I gotta take the
only person that took me-- I
guess Stephen.
>> Thank you, J.T.
>> We'll be fine.
>> Ya'll don't hate me.
>> We'll be great.
>> PROBST: Erinn, Taj, I got
nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Have fun!
>> PROBST: Head out, guys.
Enjoy.
>> Coach looked like he was
going to go without a fight, but
Erinn had to try to rub it in
his face.
I mean, she's just shooting
herself in the foot.
People are so dumb in this game.
I mean, they talk way too much.
So, it's going to hurt her and
not me.
>> It is quiet!
Love it.
>> And it's a nice, sunny day.
>> Good, there will be no shade
for Coach.
J.T. won and took Stephen on
reward, which is fine.
The guys can go out and have a
good time.
I'm not worried about it at all.
I feel very confident in my
alliance with Stephen and J.T.
We vowed that we'd go to the
final three together, and we
will.
>> Well, interesting day, if
nothing else.
I'm feeling a little guilty.
>> Why?
>> About what I said.
It was not an appropriate venue
to say that.
Like, it's a conversation I
probably should have had with
him.
>> No, no. He's a jerk.
He's a jerk.
To say, "I'm not going to eat."
Give me a break.
You're sitting here suffering
from asthma, a broken disk, this
and that, and you're not going
to eat?
>> Why wouldn't you, like, try
and make yourself feel better?
>> Oh, he's making me sick.
I'm so ready to send his ass
home.
>> I know, me, too, but...
>> And you know what kills me?
He's talking all this smack
about how he's so broken down,
but he was perfectly fine when
he was on J.T.'s heels.
Had he won, the "warrior" would
have been back.
>> Oh, I know, I know.
Yeah, I just, I don't
understand the man.
I don't understand his motives.
I would hate, hate, hate for
anything that I said today to
send me home before him.
>> Don't worry yourself.
Please don't worry.
>> Okay.
>> Do not worry.
>> My strategy definitely is to
go as far as I can with J.T.
and Stephen.
I would hate for anything I said
to have changed the way that
Stephen and J.T. view me, but
this is really the time where
you do start to get really
paranoid about this stuff.
(bird screeches)
>> This is going to be like a
vacation for me.
A little sun tan out here...
All those wishy-washy people at
camp with no character. Phew!
Coach Wade's foundation is built
on a rock.
Inside here...
Unbreakable, unbending,
unyielding, immeasurable,
immovable, invincible.
Staying out here for a week
without any food will only
make me a better, stronger
person.
Those guys won't be able to get
old Coach Wade down, I'll tell
you that.
I will not have anything to eat.
It's going to be like the
ancient American Indians that
are my ancestors.
They used to go out into the
wilderness for 48 hours and
they would commune with the
creator of the universe and they
would become men.
Well, I'm already a man.
So, this will just make me more
of a man, but this is going to
be an adventure.
Thank you for creating me as an
individual.
I ask that you would help me to
forgive Erinn as she's back at
camp thinking negative thoughts
about me.
At the challenge, Erinn said,
"Well, I think Coach is just
being a martyr."
But I just let her have it.
Dragon slayer makes his dragon
cane.
Whether it's because I'm
speaking such truth that nobody
can deny it or because I'm so
eloquent, whatever the case, I
got the last word.
And I hope she goes home next.
She's certainly going to get my
vote.
Coach Wade's body might be
failing him in many ways, but
Coach Wade still has what it
takes to outlast anybody out
here in this environment.
Period, paragraph.
>> Oh, man!
>> Oh, wow.
This is how I like to travel.
>> When I woke up this morning,
I never would have imagined I'd
be in a private plane.
>> Look at this.
This is the freaking life.
>> This was the best reward I
could have possibly asked for.
A private plane to, uh, the
governor's retreat.
I just really soaked it up.
That's always been a dream of
mine, have a private plane and
to be able to fly on one like
that, and it was really awesome.
>> Ha-ha! Whoo!
>> Hey, we're getting low.
Good job, guys.
>> Thank you.
>> Oh, man!
>> Hello.
>> Hey.
>> Welcome to Pousada Cantao,
the governor's retreat.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Oh, man, this is nice.
>> This is ridiculous.
>> I mean, this place is just
beautiful.
You can tell there were some
big parties thrown at this
place.
>> Here it is.
>> All right, thank you.
Whoo!
>> You're welcome.
>> We were taken to our room.
Oh, my God, a bed, a shower.
>> Oh, wow!
Oh, my gosh!
This is what I look like! Wow!
That is a beard, all right.
I think it'd look good with a
little trim.
>> Look at my hair, man.
>> When we stepped into the
bathroom, we looked at
ourselves in the mirror and
that was a shock.
I mean, I haven't seen myself
in over a month.
Oh, my God.
My teeth are gross now.
>> I need to take a shower.
>> Shower, I know.
>> Yeah.
I was like, man, I've got to
get a shower, get out of here.
So, oh, man, it was like
heaven.
Oh!
Oh, man!
I can't get enough of this soap.
34 days.
I have not washed my nasty self.
Oh!
>> As soon as we were clean, we
left our room and went for our
feast.
>> What you're gonna have
tonight is authentic Brazilian
churrasco.
>> Oh, yes!
>> It's a Brazilian barbecue
with many kinds of meat.
Eat as much as you want.
>> Thank you so much.
>> See you later.
>> Oh, wow! Oh, wow!
>> Yes!
Feliz navidad.
>> Oh, wow!
Oh, my God!
This meat is incredible.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, my!
>> Is there more?
>> Por favor.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yeah.
We were having a meat festival.
We had steaks, we had pork, we
had a grilled pineapple.
We were filling up and,
basically, by the time we were
done with the meats, we were
stuffed.
(sighs)
>> Well, buddy...
>> Cheers.
>> To the final two in this
game.
>> Final two.
Ah.
>> I mean, we got this thing,
man.
There's no reason why you and I
aren't sitting in the final two.
>> Coach totally depends on us.
>> Coach is totally with us, and
I will take Coach to the final
three.
>> Today at the reward
challenge, Erinn goes on a
little bit of a rant about how
"Well, Coach doesn't want to
have to perform in the next
immunity challenge and he's
giving himself excuses."
There was no reason to sort
of rub salt in his wound.
She can't really control what
she says, which is not a great
trait in a potential ally.
Erinn doing that, it kind of
makes me want to keep her less.
What is that going to do for
her?
I mean, it's just not
strategic.
>> You can never tell, man.
>> That's-That's when people get
screwed over.
>> And hopefully, she's going to
get screwed over.
>> My exile experience was
no sleep, starving.
No food.
Very little water.
And it was friggin' awesome.
It was a great experience to be
out here and once again test
myself and have nothing.
I've been in the Amazon, the
Congo, the Oronoco, the Darien
Gap...
Chalk another one to the list.
The dunes at Exile.
Yes, I'm walking slower.
Yes, my asthma is still at the
forefront of things.
Yes, it's going to take me
longer to get to the challenge
today.
I do not feel tired.
I do not feel hungry.
I feel nothing but incredible
mental focus on the task at
hand which I have to
accomplish today and that's
winning immunity.
Marcus Aurelius once said,
"Through our greatest
adversities come our greatest
successes."
I plan on winning immunity
today.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
We'll now bring in Coach,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Oh, my God. Coach.
>> What's up, fellas?
>> You look beat.
Come on, bring it in.
>> Ladies. I'm feeling great.
I'm feeling great.
>> When Coach returned from
Exile with his cane and he's
limping and I'm thinking, "This
guy is such a drama queen.
He's so dramatic."
Any 37-year-old man who thinks
he's a dragon slayer belongs in
a mental institution.
They need to come get him.
When we have Tribal Council,
he'll be free and they can take
him home.
>> PROBST: How did it go down?
>> I was freezing, I didn't get
any sleep, I didn't have any
water, no food, no fire.
I had the best time of my life.
It was euphoric.
>> PROBST: All right. You guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Stephen, take back the immunity
necklace.
>> Hey, can I get some water?
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to use your arms to brace
yourself between two walls
while your feet are positioned
on very narrow footholds.
Every 15 minutes, you'll move
to an even smaller foothold,
and you'll be doing this
barefoot.
When you reach the third and
final foothold, you will stay
there for as long as you can.
When you fall off, you're out.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, is guaranteed a
one-in-four shot of winning
this game.
Losers, Tribal Council,
somebody going home.
We'll take our spots.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
All right, everybody's got
their arms inside the frame.
Their feet on the first peg.
This challenge is underway.
You cannot use your butt, your
back, or your hips to lean
against the wall to give you
support.
This is where mental toughness
is going to win out.
All right, we're going to get
ready to move to the next
smaller foothold.
I'm going to count you into
this.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Take your time.
Get yourself settled.
Everybody's looking good.
Coach, you think the time you
spent on Exile meditating may
have conveniently prepared you
for a challenge like this?
>> Deep down inside the pit of
every man's stomach is a
feeling that he's no longer
going to be invincible.
So, for me to go out there and
to put myself in the most
extreme situation that I could,
I did it because I wanted for
my mind to once and for all
tell my body that you still
have it.
>> PROBST: Perfect opportunity
to put that philosophy to the
test in this challenge.
Because this is about mind over
matter.
And it will get difficult.
All right, we're going to now
move to the final foothold.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Erinn drops out before getting
on the final foothold.
Erinn will take a spot on the
bench.
No shot at immunity, vulnerable
at Tribal Council tonight.
There's no time limit now.
This goes until only one
person's left standing.
There's no way to prepare for a
challenge like this physically.
This is all in your head.
Stephen drops out.
Take a spot on the bench.
Taj digging in.
Taj cannot hang on any longer.
Taj is out of the challenge.
We are down to two.
J.T. and Coach.
The listener and the talker.
The young buck, the older
warrior, battling it out for a
guaranteed spot in the final
four.
>> Got any food, Jeff?
>> PROBST: If I wheeled out a
big old steak and a six-pack,
you'd step down?
>> Probably so, Jeff.
>> Well, then you might as well
step down, unless you're trying
to vote me off tonight.
>> I can't believe you don't
trust me, Coach.
>> I do trust you.
I trust you implicitly, J.T.
You know that.
>> Good.
>> You are a man of your word.
Few and far are those left in
this world.
>> PROBST: This is just how you
want it, isn't it, Coach?
Battle against the best.
You've been talking about it
for 36 days.
You're getting it today.
Been up there 50 minutes now.
You're going to have to fight
the pain.
Your feet will recover.
No way to recover if you're
voted out.
>> You ain't going to let me
try the necklace on, are you,
Coach?
>> Nope.
>> I don't blame you.
>> I got something to prove
coming back from Exile.
(screams)
>> PROBST: Coach steps down.
>> That's all right.
>> PROBST: J.T. has won
individual immunity.
>> Oh, my God, man.
Geez, are you okay, man?
You did awesome.
>> Be hard-headed.
Get up. Come on.
>> Are you okay?
>> My back was... my back was
spasming up there.
>> Can you stand up now, though?
>> Oh, man.
You did an incredible...
>> Come on, stand up.
>> You don't have to stand up
if you can't yet.
>> PROBST: Where are you feeling
it?
>> My back spasmed while I was
up there the last ten minutes.
>> Oh, my God, man.
>> I felt something go.
I tried. I couldn't do it.
>> PROBST: You going to want
medical to look at that?
>> Nope, nobody is taking me
out of the game right now.
If medical would really look at
my back, I wouldn't be here, so,
no, please don't have them look
at my back.
>> PROBST: J.T.,
congratulations.
(applause)
J.T. is safe at tonight's Tribal
Council.
Coach, Stephen, Taj, Erinn, one
of the four of you going home
after 36 long days out here.
Grab your stuff and head back
to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> Could have gone a lot longer,
huh?
>> Yeah.
>> I figured that.
>> It looked like Coach had
really been suffering.
You know, he looked like Exile
had really been tough.
You know, I definitely felt bad
for the guy.
But, you know, Coach is still
the dragon slayer and a really
strong competitor.
If I want to win this game,
I want people I can beat in the
finals.
(thunder rumbles)
>> Well, congratulations.
>> Nice job.
>> You all right, Coach? Huh?
>> Coach was really ridiculous
today.
I mean, he walks in like he can
barely move, and then he's
standing up on these things
for, like, near an hour.
>> He's an interesting man,
right there.
>> Yeah.
>> He's so full of it.
>> I know.
He's been walking around since
we've been back, like, you're
not as broken down as you're
trying to make yourself look.
And, really, like, I'm ready
for him to go home.
And the other thing, too, when
Jeff asked him if he wanted
medical to look at him.
>> Yeah.
>> No, you don't want them to
look at it because they're going
to tell you there's nothing
wrong with you.
>> There's absolutely nothing
>> He needed an excuse for not
winning.
>> That was a classic struggle
today, man.
How much longer could you have
gone?
>> Probably 30 minutes.
>> As iron sharpens iron, so one
man sharpens another.
Our ancestors would hope and
pray for somebody worthy in
battle to defeat them, and I
think that that definitely
played out today with J.T. and
myself.
I was honored by the defeat and
the way that I went down.
>> Stephen and I are leaning
towards Erinn.
I know Erinn is going to vote
for you.
Taj may-- you may get two votes.
But Stephen and I and you
vote Erinn, she's gone.
>> J.T. reassures me, tells me,
hey, everything's cool, man.
Don't worry-- Erinn needs to go
tonight because of the comment
that she made the other day.
It was unforgivable.
It's just her time to go.
It's been her time to go for
a while.
I mean, sending me to Exile,
supposedly, mentally, I'm
supposed to be down, so she's
trying to kick me while I'm
on the ground.
>> Oh, yeah, that's it.
That's all she's doing.
>> And you know, a lot of my
bravado is just 'cause I'm
trying to tell myself, hey,
you're still kind of the man.
>> Guys.
>> Hey, come on down.
>> So you really want to send
Erinn home tonight?
>> I was really pissed off.
When she went to Exile we were
all, like, patting her on the
back.
We weren't trying to kick her,
because, you know, I mean--
I just thought it was, like, so
tasteless and classless.
J.T. and I sat down with Coach
and we reassured him that
the warrior alliance was good.
Erinn was going home tonight.
And J.T. is going to vote for
Erinn because he feels like he
promised Coach that he would.
But I don't know what I'm going
to do.
I don't... I mean, it's really
tricky right now.
>> She tried to call me out in
the very beginning, and I was
like, those are the kind of
people that get their ass voted
out.
>> Right, because no one trusts
them.
>> Brendan did it.
Tyson started getting sketchy.
>> Well, Erinn belongs right
beside them.
>> And you're totally cool with
that?
I mean, I'm just asking, right?
I mean, there's not going to be
any surprises tonight, right?
>> No.
>> I'm done with the surprises
at Tribal, man.
The warrior alliance is still
going strong.
I surrounded myself with strong
players, and to this date, it
has not backfired on me.
It looks like through all the
blindsides, Coach Wade will be
the last tribe member left of
what used to be Timbira.
I am the last of the Mohicans.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Brendan, Tyson, Sierra, and
Debbie, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
So, Coach let's start with your
stay on Exile Island.
When J.T. picked you to go to
Exile, you made your big thing,
about, "I'm going to do this
the hard way."
Erinn, you didn't like that.
>> I didn't.
Like, he's weak and he's this
and he's that and then to go off
and not eat or drink for three
days, that just really rubbed
me the wrong way, and it just
minimized the entire experience
that the rest of us were having.
>> PROBST: Was there a part of
you that had just come off one
of the roughest stays on Exile,
feeling a little bit like you're
going to upstage me with your
dramatic exile?
>> Oh, God, yeah. Yeah.
Like, the time that I spent out
there sucked.
It was the worst thing I've
ever done.
I never want to do it again.
And you're standing there
going, "Oh, I totally want to
do that; that sounds awesome."
Like, that sucks.
>> PROBST: Coach, you respect
what Erinn's saying?
>> I think that everybody here
that's been to Exile had a much
tougher time than me.
But I had past experiences with
which to draw on.
Which made it easier for me,
and, you know, a lot of times,
men drop what they think is a
pebble, but women see a boulder
dropping and crashing, an
overwhelming sense of judgment.
I certainly wasn't trying to
minimize her experience or
anybody else's for that matter.
So there's really nothing else
to say, you know.
Mark Twain-- "Better for people
to think you're a fool than
to open your mouth and remove
all doubt."
I've already done that.
I really don't have any place to
go now.
>> PROBST: Erinn, you feel
pretty secure about your
alliance?
>> I never feel secure, ever.
>> PROBST: Do you think the
person going home tonight may
know it's coming, or is this
going to be a shock?
>> For the most part, someone
will be surprised, yes.
>> PROBST: Coach, you think it's
going to be a surprise tonight?
>> No.
>> PROBST: Based on what?
>> Women have great intuition.
>> PROBST: So you're saying it's
already been said tonight if we
listened?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: All right, it is
time to get to the vote.
>> One more thing.
>> PROBST: Yes?
>> I wrote a poem for everybody
to hear.
With friend and foe we march to
the battle plane
Some to seek success,
others to seek fame
We play with honor for the love
of this game
And with armor or without,
we will toil in vain
So that someday, someone,
somewhere will remember our
name.
>> PROBST: Can't think of a
better way to lead us into the
vote.
J.T., you keeping that idol?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
J.T.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
J.T., you're up.
>> Dragon slayed.
>> You've been like the cat
that had nine lives in this
game.
Good job staying in the game
this long, kid.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, tonight is the last
night you can do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Coach.
Erinn.
One vote Coach, one vote Erinn.
Two votes Erinn, one vote Coach.
Coach.
We're tied.
Two votes Coach, two votes
Erinn, one vote left.
12th person voted out and the
fifth member of our jury...
Coach.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> It was an honor, guys.
Thank you.
>> PROBST: Coach, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> PROBST: Well, it's clear
based on the number of
blindsides at Tribal Council,
this is going to be a really fun
finish.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> J.T. ended up voting with
Coach for strategic reasons.
>> PROBST: J.T. and Stephen turn
on each other.
>> I probably could come off
as a villain.
>> Either way it's done.
>> PROBST: And with only four
left, all bets are off.
>> This is a game for a
million dollars.
You have to be ruthless.
>> PROBST: Join us for the
exciting season finale.
>> There was some sadness
tonight as I left.
I cannot imagine why someone
would want to keep Erinn over
me in the warrior alliance,
but obviously somebody turned.
Judging by their reaction, it
was Stephen.
The wizard was definitely not
the white wizard.
He was the evil wizard in the
end.
It was a travesty.
Death before dishonor, and I did
not dishonor myself.
I feel good about how I played
the game.