>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Two tribes-- Jalapao in red and
Timbira in black-- were stranded
in Brazil's Tocantins.
Take a look around-- Brazilian
highlands.
Beautiful part of Brazil,
but extremely harsh.
(thunder rumbles)
One person from each tribe is
not going to make this journey.
Based only on first impressions,
the tribes believed they were
voting out one of their own.
>> Zebra-striped top.
>> Sierra, head over.
>> Older lady.
>> PROBST: Sandy, you can't be
happy about this.
>> I'm pissed.
>> PROBST: But the game wasn't
over for Sandy and Sierra.
They had only been voted off the
trek.
They were flown to their tribe
camps in a helicopter, leaving
their unhappy tribe mates to
walk for hours.
>> This thing is getting heavy.
I mean, really heavy.
>> PROBST: Alone in their
camps, Sandy and Sierra
discovered a clue to a hidden
immunity idol.
>> People may think this is a
really stupid idea, but...
>> PROBST: Instead of searching
for the idol, Sierra decided to
win over the Timbira tribe with
hard work, which might have
succeeded.
>> Well, you know, Sierra, we
all love her.
>> PROBST: Or not.
>> But even though she's
awesome, she's got to go.
>> PROBST: Sandy searched for
the idol at Jalapao and came up
short.
>> Wonder what a pace is.
>> PROBST: Putting her in
danger.
Carolina struggling to stay up.
(cheering)
But when Jalapao suffered their
first loss...
Jalapao, Tribal Council tonight.
The first person will be voted
out of this game, and it's
coming from your tribe.
...Sandy was in deep trouble.
But Carolina's bossiness...
>> Let's try to get everything
done as soon as possible.
When it comes to, like,
working, I can get very
opinionated.
>> PROBST: ...made for a
surprise decision.
Carolina, the tribe has spoken.
Sandy narrowly escaped.
Can she survive another week?
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Look around the outside of...
(chattering quietly)
>> It's not like we just picked
randomly.
>> No, I know.
>> I made it through Tribal
Council by a landslide.
I think Carolina played her, uh,
cards terribly wrong, and so
she's kept me in this game so
far.
(Sandy laughs)
Lord, thank you!
That's our boy.
He said, "We're going to have
fire," didn't you, honey?
I believe I'm underestimated in
this game.
I want to win this thing.
And as long as I'm here, I can
win it.
Thank you all so much for
letting me hang in here with
you all for a few more days.
>> We just did what's best for
the team, you know.
>> Oh, thank you so much.
>> Now that Carolina is out, I
mean, we all pretty much agreed
that she just swapped places
with Sandy.
Sandy was going to be first
and then Carolina after that.
Now Carolina was first and now
Sandy after that.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Feel how soft.
>> Let me have a bite of that,
Joe.
>> Try that.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Maybe a little longer,
I think.
>> We need some protein.
We need protein in a bad way
right now.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> I don't know if the whole
tribe's up for it, but we're
going to eat some termites
today.
All right, so there was a
couple of mounds over here.
There's a mound right there.
>> Should we just open them up
and pick them up?
>> Most definitely.
>> All right, ready?
>> Yeah.
>> Ew, what's all them,
termites?
>> Oh, yeah, those are termites.
>> Oh, that's wild.
>> I've never been in a
situation where I've been
deprived of food for a long
period of time.
I'm a teenager, and I'm used to
having those, those comfort
foods at home, where if I'm
hungry, I can eat whenever I
want.
And out here, if I want a
snack, I'm going to have to go
find something.
Nuh-uh, buddy, you're coming to
Papa.
(Joe grunts)
>> Ah, ay-yo!
Holy cow!
Look at that big one!
>> I got to have that for
fishing.
>> Oh, get... no, no.
Eat that.
>> Just throw it in there.
>> Okay, all right.
>> Sweet mother of...
Hey, Steve!
>> Should we cut it first or
just bite into it?
>> Eat it.
>> Bite the head off.
>> You want the head or the
tail?
>> He wants to bite the head
off.
>> Just me and you splitting it?
>> Get you some, man.
>> Ooh.
>> Oh, God.
>> It's tough.
(groaning)
>> Whoo!
>> Oh, that's nasty.
>> Your teeth are covered.
>> Oh, God.
It's tough, man.
You got to chew.
Bite it. Bite it.
>> Bite that sucker.
I love it!
>> Maybe I'll just wait.
>> I didn't try the worm.
After I saw Stephen's face...
(groans)
Uh-uh.
I mean, I'll eat one at a
challenge if I need to, but not
in real life.
>> So good, so good.
>> Gonna go, like, one of those.
Come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on.
on, come on.
Don't.
All right, breakfast is after
noon.
(chuckles)
>> Day one, my tribe tried to
vote me out.
I think they all perceive me
as the weakest link.
And instead, I came here and
there was a clue for a hidden
immunity idol, but I haven't
had a chance to look for it.
I'm still on the outs in my
tribe, so I most definitely
need to find it.
And I need someone to help me
with that.
In this game, you need people
on your side.
And Brendan's the one person
that didn't vote for me.
So he was the one I trusted the
most.
>> I'm glad you did.
Thank you.
Oh, really?
All right, but totally got
your back.
Sierra needed some help to
figure this out.
I think she didn't necessarily
feel comfortable that the tribe
was not going to vote her off
in the first Tribal Council,
and I think it's important
taking a look for.
It can't hurt.
>> The first clue, it said,
"The stick marks the spot on
your biggest beach.
Dig for a while and assistance
you'll reach."
Oh, I got it!
Oh, my God.
Okay.
"With your back to the river,
walk towards the lone tree.
Dig after ten paces at the
place where you'll be."
>> Yeah.
>> We'll probably figure it out
when we get there.
>> Should I go check on Brendan
and Sierra and make sure
they're still alive?
>> Go.
I'll wait here.
>> I just wanted to make sure
you all were alive.
Cool!
I love it!
Oh, how cool is this?
You guys have worked your tails
off.
>> Debbie caught us.
Luckily, Sierra had the idea of
saying that we're building a
fire pit, which I thought that
was really smart.
Uh, and just kind of went with
it.
>> This is so cool.
This will be fun.
>> It'll be good, right?
>> Yeah!
We can pretend we're at the
beach somewhere.
>> Debbie's so fun-loving.
She was all about it.
I mean, she was our best
salesperson.
>> Wait till you see what
Brendan and Sierra built.
A massive fire pit for a
big beach fire tonight.
>> Really?
>> I just don't think it makes
that much sense.
I probably won't go, you know.
I'd rather sit around here and
talk crap.
>> All right.
>> We were so close to getting
caught.
It may be a stupid move, but to
tell you the truth, I don't
think it worth it to continue
looking for the hidden
immunity idol, even though I
know where I stand in this camp
with these people, and I'm
really worried about my
position.
>> Are you hungry?
>> I was thinking I really want
to steam, like, big, like, sea
bass with, like, some olive oil
and fresh lime juice and wrap it
up in aluminum foil and just let
it steam.
Are you serious?
(laughs)
>> Are we going to do rice
at the same time?
>> That's fine with me.
>> The problem with that though
is with the beans, you got to
have them in water.
What happens with the rice is
that the rice soaks it all up,
and I'm afraid you're gonna
burn stuff.
>> You can just add water as
you go.
>> Think it's gonna be
undercooked or it's gonna be
overcooked.
>> Do you want to cook?
I'm gonna tell you right now.
It's either gonna be under-
or overcooked.
>> You know what, we've been
waiting three days to eat.
If I wait 20 more minutes for
rice to get cooked, it doesn't
matter to me.
But you're the one doing the
cooking, so...
>> I'm just telling you it's
not gonna be perfect.
>> You want to put everything
in the same pot.
So you guys want to do that,
no problem.
Candace, she has a personality
like mine.
She looks to find faults in
other people.
I do it because I'm-I'm a coach,
and I do it because that's my
job.
And I think that maybe she just
does it 'cause that's her
nature.
>> You're taking out, um, I
think, some frustration...
>> No, you're taking out
frustration.
You asked my opinion about the
rice and beans.
That's what I think.
>> I am an educated woman, and I
don't take crap from people.
And Coach comes over feeling
like he's the expert.
In real life, like, I would have
broke it down, like, to his
psyche, you know, and his
insecurities and how he
overcompensates.
I would've... I would've really,
like, got to him.
But here, I walked away, took a
breath, worked on something
else because I knew he was
gonna feel insecure and want to
apologize because he was wrong.
>> I don't want to fight with
you.
>> I just want to kiss you...
>> Stop. See? You're so full of
it.
>> No, listen...
>> Seriously, I don't even know
if you're being serious.
>> I am being serious.
>> You agreed that you took it
out on me.
>> And I apologize, and you
apologize for coming at me a
little bit strong.
>> (laughs): I did not even come
at you strong.
I was just keeping it real.
>> A little... a little...
>> You can kiss right here.
Okay, that's good.
That man's got a ego bigger than
Brazil.
That will be the death of him,
is his ego.
>> Everywhere is smutty.
>> We can't stay clean over
here.
Y'all, seriously, I don't look
this rough normally.
When I clean up I'm so cute.
I promise you.
My husband will tell you...
>> What's your husband do?
>> Oh, really?
>> He-he gets all the
information and stuff.
>> Is he college or...?
>> College and NFL.
>> Nice. Eddie...? Last name?
What's your last name?
>> George.
>> Eddie George?
>> You're married to Eddie
George?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> The Ohio State Buckeye
Heisman Trophy winner?
>> Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
>> That's your husband?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Are you serious?
>> I'm so serious.
>> I...
>> (laughs)
>> Oh, my God.
>> Eddie George is a former NFL
running back.
He retired a few years ago from
the NFL.
And he also won the Heisman
Trophy back in college.
Uh, it's a pretty neat deal to
be on a tribe in Survivor with,
uh, Eddie George's wife.
Eddie George is not your
husband.
>> He's my husband.
(laughs)
>> I absolutely have no idea who
Eddie George is.
So while everybody around me is
freaking out, I'm feeling like
an absolute idiot.
>> You just changed your whole
perspective to everybody.
>> I've got a completely
different outlook on Taj.
Her husband's a very famous
football player.
So, you know, she's probably got
a lot more money than I do.
>> I hate to judge anybody by
how much money they have, but I
know I definitely need the
million dollars more than Taj
does.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Timbira getting your first look
at the new Jalapao Tribe.
Carolina voted out at the first
Tribal Council.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Absolutely.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: As the rain comes
down to welcome us.
First things first.
Jerry, I will take back
immunity.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, three
members of each tribe will race
through the water to grab a
ball.
You'll then work together until
you can shoot the ball into your
basket, while members of the
other tribe attempt to stop you
any way they can.
The matchups will be determined
randomly, with an equal number
of men and women in each round.
First tribe to score three
baskets wins immunity and
something else.
>> Come on, baby, come on.
>> PROBST: I know you're hungry.
This should help: fishing gear.
Everything you need: spear, two
poles; you got line, tackle
box, a mask, knife.
This should change things back
at camp significantly.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Big-time.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will send one
member from the losing tribe
to Exile Island.
Good news: waiting for you on
Exile, the clue to the location
of a hidden immunity idol.
And there is a twist to Exile,
which I will read after the
challenge.
A lot at stake.
Worth playing for?
>> OTHERS: Yeah!
>> PROBST: Timbira, you have one
extra member.
Who are you gonna sit out?
>> I'll sit out.
>> Debra, you'll take a spot on
the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you
a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
>> Come on.
(thunder crashing)
>> PROBST: All right, first
round, Taj, Stephen, and Sydney
for Jalapao taking on Sierra,
Candace, and Tyson for Timbira.
Here we go.
Go!
>> (yelling)
>> PROBST: Stephen quickly out
for Jalapao.
Taj trying to block out Tyson.
Tyson takes down Stephen and
passes off to Taj.
A wild shot!
(indistinct shouting)
Tyson has it for Timbira, over
to Sierra.
Sierra and Taj are fighting for
it now.
Stephen getting in on it.
Taj comes up with it for
Jalapao.
Candace intercepts for Timbira.
Timbira scores!
>> Whoo! All right!
>> PROBST: Timbira leads
one-zip.
>> (shouts indistinctly)
>> PROBST: All right, next
round, it is J.T., Joe, and
Sandy for Jalapao taking on
Erinn, Brendon, and Tyson
for Timbira.
Timbira leads one-zip.
Go!
Brendon and Joe going at it.
(indistinct shouting)
Joe dives for it.
Brendon comes up with it.
Brendon over to Tyson for
Timbira.
Tyson fakes J.T.
J.T. takes Tyson down.
Big takedown.
J.T. not letting Tyson get rid
of that ball.
Another takedown by J.T.
Tyson gets rid of it to Brendon.
Joe now trying to take Brendon
down.
Erinn and Sandy are tied up at
the other end.
Brendon gets away from Joe.
Brendon with a long shot, just
short.
Tyson with a shot for Timbira.
Timbira scores and now leads
two-zip.
>> All right, guys!
>> PROBST: Next round, all
women.
Candace, Sierra, and Erinn for
Timbira taking on Taj, Sydney,
and Sandy for Jalapao.
Timbira leads two-zip.
We are playing to three.
Timbira could win it right here.
Go!
Sierra and Sydney fight for the
ball.
Sierra has it.
Sydney takes her down.
Candace takes both of them down.
Four women all fighting for that
ball.
Taj now getting in on it.
Sierra holding on to it.
>> Hold on to it, Sierra!
Hold on to it, Sierra!
(indistinct shouting)
>> PROBST: Taj takes it from
Sierra.
It's Taj and Candace now.
Taj throwing Candace off of her!
Taj has a free run.
Can she make it count?
No!
>> Get it, Candace!
>> PROBST: Candace now has it
for Timbira.
Candace with a long shot.
Bounces back to Taj.
She's short.
Sydney puts it in!
Sydney keeping Jalapao alive.
Timbira now leads two-one.
Timbira still one basket away
for the win.
Next round, three men from each
tribe.
J.T., Joe, and Spencer for
Jalapao taking on Brendon,
Coach, and Jerry for Timbira.
Timbira leads two-one.
Here we go.
Go!
>> Go! Come on, Timbira!
>> PROBST: Joe and Brendon
racing for it.
Joe tries to skip it along.
It won't work.
Brendon has it for Timbira.
He's carrying Joe.
Brendon with a wild pass to
Jerry.
J.T. gets it for Jalapao.
Coach is really dragging.
J.T. fakes out Jerry...
and scores for Jalapao!
We are tied two-two.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Next round, Stephen,
Sydney, and Taj taking on
Sierra, Candace, and Tyson.
We are tied two-two.
We're playing to three.
Winner of this point wins reward
and immunity.
>> Let's go, Taj!
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Tyson!
Go, Tyson!
>> PROBST: Stephen and Tyson
going at it.
Sydney has it for Jalapao.
Sierra takes her down.
Tosses to Taj.
Taj and Candace going at it.
Sydney takes it from Taj.
Sierra holding her down.
(indistinct shouting)
Sydney passes to Taj.
Candace trying to take Taj down.
>> Get it, Tyson!
>> PROBST: Tyson has it for
Timbira.
>> Go, Tyson!
>> PROBST: A wild shot!
Does no good.
>> Let's go, Sydney!
>> PROBST: Sierra has it.
This could win it.
No!
Stephen pulls Tyson down.
Sydney has it for Jalapao.
Just misses.
(thunder crashing)
(indistinct shouting)
Stephen has it for Jalapao, but
he can't get a shot off.
>> Get loose! Get loose!
>> PROBST: Stephen breaks free.
Could win it for Jalapao.
And he scores!
Jalapao wins immunity and
reward!
♪ ♪
Jalapao, congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Big decision you have
to make, Jalapao.
You're now gonna send one member
of Timbira to Exile Island.
>> PROBST: Brendan, grab your
stuff; head over.
Now to the twist I told you
about earlier.
I have a very wet, but still
effective note.
It says to Brendan: "Choose one
member of the winning tribe to
join you at Exile Island."
>> PROBST: It's Taj and Brendan,
opposite tribes, together on
Exile.
Could be interesting.
Here is a map to Exile.
You will return to the game in
time for the next Tribal
Council.
I know you guys want this,
Jalapao.
>> Yeah, thank you!
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
>> It's beautiful!
>> PROBST: Jalapao, grab your
reward.
Head back to camp.
Happy fishing.
Timbira, got nothing for you
except a date with me at Tribal
Council.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
You have tonight and tomorrow
to figure out who is going home.
>> Our tribe's going to Tribal
Council, so we're going to have
to take somebody out.
Sierra's probably the one to go.
She didn't make the trek with
us at the beginning.
I mean, she's trying, but it
looks like she's numero uno on
the chopping block.
>> One, two, three!
>> Jalapao!
>> Today we won immunity and
fishing gear, which included a
casting net, a couple fishing
poles, a spear and some hooks
and stuff like that, so
we're looking forward to
spending our day without Tribal
Council going to try to find
some fish.
We need a physical challenge
like that.
>> To be the winning tribe
feels phenomenal.
If we lost immunity, there was
probably a 50% chance of me
going home.
But we won, and I'm here for
another several more days.
>> A net-- a cast net.
>> Just ease out here about
waist deep.
We have to figure out how to
throw it so it spreads out when
it hits and you can catch bait
fish that way.
>> J.T. has definitely emerged
as our tribe leader and
honestly, I'm thrilled to be out
here with him.
He's like no one I would
have met back at home and I
think we're getting to know each
other, which I thought is sort
of surprising because he's the
Alabama country boy.
He is Tom Sawyer, and I am the
angsty city boy.
He might just be seducing me
with his pretty country ways,
but I'm smitten.
>> You take the loose end...
>> Yeah.
>> You go back through that
hole and back through that hole
you just created.
>> I see.
>> What you'll do is just hold
it until you feel them, and
then just snatch it.
Stephen and I come from
different walks of life.
He's definitely a city boy and
I'm an south Alabama cattle
farmer.
But we get along really well.
So we have a good friendship.
>> I'm going to become the
greatest spear fisherman that
ever existed.
Oh, my God!
They're right here.
There was, like, four or five
of them.
We had some luck in seeing fish.
Not so much in catching the
fish, but I think the fishing
trip was successful in
cementing my and J.T.'s
friendship.
And I know that it makes me look
like his goofy, awkward,
right-hand man.
But if he thinks I'm the goofy,
awkward right-hand man, he's
going to want to keep me around
longer.
There's something inside here.
>> When Jalapao tribe picked me
to go to Exile, I was totally
psyched.
I wanted the chance to get the
immunity idol.
Rice, awesome.
And also to come to Exile with
somebody from the other tribe
is a great opportunity to learn
some information.
>> "You must each choose an
urn."
>> You go first.
>> All right.
Once Brendan and I made it to
Exile Island, we found two
urns, and there was a message
that we both had to choose one.
There's nothing in mine.
>> Uh-oh.
"Open in private."
>> Oh, crap!
>> Can you give me a moment?
>> Take a second.
We only have two cups.
>> "Congratulations.
You now have the clue to hidden
immunity idol.
It's up to you whether you
share this information with
anyone else."
I opened up my cup and it had
two notes in it.
The first note was the first
clue to find the immunity idol.
"If you want to be safe, snoop
around, take a peek, but in
tribal homelands is the thing
that you seek."
The tribal homelands?
I kind of look at this as an
awesome thing to get sent to
Exile this early in the game.
I just have to figure out where
the tribal homelands are.
"Also you have a choice before
you.
At the end of your stay at
Exile, you can return to the
tribe you just left or you
can join the other tribe.
This is a big decision.
It has potential to turn this
game on its head."
That it does.
The second note was saying that
I had the ability to switch
tribes.
No chance, no chance I'll go
to Jalapao.
Let me see it. I just want to
see what it looks like.
...with writing on it.
I'm gonna go take a walk,
though.
>> Do you want me to help you
find it?
It's yours.
>> You can walk with me, yeah.
>> Yeah, I don't want to sit
here by myself.
I'm working Brendan to give
myself a chance to find the
idol.
So I'm like trying to be real
nice.
I'm playing up the friendly
aspect because when my tribe
found out who my husband
actually is-- Eddie George from
the NFL-- I could just tell
that they were thinking,
"Well, she doesn't need this.
We need it."
Everybody thinks they have a
great cause.
Hell, my cause is I want it and
I'm going to stay here and get
it.
"If you want to be safe, snoop
around, take a peek, but in the
tribal homelands is the thing
that you seek."
>> Does that make any sense?
>> I think our homelands are
where we live.
>> Oh, you're right.
At that point, when I realized
the idol was somewhere back at
the tribe camps, I was thinking
there's two hidden immunity
idols.
There's one in our camp, and
one in Jalapao's camp, and it's
not the same idol that Sierra
was looking for.
Do you have, like, a buddy on
your team?
>> I haven't really bonded with
anyone yet.
So we have to bond.
>> Seriously, I'm all for that.
>> We have to bond.
>> So when you go back, will you
tell other people it's in your
homeland?
>> Probably not.
See, I'm thinking I need to save
myself from my tribe.
>> Yeah.
I'm an entrepreneur, and
having your own business, you
have to make people understand
who you are and make them feel
that, you know what, we can
work together.
And Taj and I created a great
bond that could be very helpful
for both of us if we do get to
the merge.
So if we do rendezvous later in
the game, I think we will have
a relationship in place.
The goal is that we both get to
get sent back here.
>> That's perfect.
>> Hopefully, that will give us
the next clue where it is in
our homeland.
So we need to work together.
>> Yeah.
>> Does that work?
>> That works for me.
We're going to try it.
>> That works?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You guys, this is really
good.
>> You got a big chunk out of
your elbow right there.
>> That's where that young kid
tackled me, man.
>> I am shocked at that little
old lady.
>> Yeah, they almost drowned me
at one point.
>> It was a very tough
challenge, and it got really
physical.
So when we lost, I was very
disappointed.
I hate to lose because
somebody is going home.
>> Honestly, I didn't see Coach
playing that hard.
He barely tackled anyone.
He didn't fight to get free.
We need action, not words.
>> I feel like I'm dealing with
one of the, like, church women
at my church that go every
Sunday and wear these hats,
but they ain't on the up-and-up.
That's what I feel like, you
know.
Coach is not excelling
physically in the way that
I thought he would.
And at the end of the day, I
really don't see, like, what
all Coach is bringing to the
table except a lot of talk.
>> You know what I mean,
big-time right now.
I don't know.
I just... I don't like to be
around negativity, and if we've
got negative going on in the
group, it's going to be
really tough for me.
>> This kind of stuff that
you're telling me makes me
worried because who would go?
>> I thought earlier we'd all
decided Sierra.
>> Yeah, I know, but what I'm
thinking is this: I do want
the strong people to be here,
but I mean the poisoned apple
needs to go because it's going
to ruin the bunch.
At first I thought I'm going
with the plan and vote for
Sierra, and now Candace is...
boy, talk about cancer on the
team.
Just the negative attitude, I
think everybody's pretty much
fed up with it.
And, you know, sometimes there
is addition by subtraction.
She got on me.
She's going to get on everybody.
The cancer will ruin the tribe.
>> Oh, man, my man!
>> Hey!
>> All right!
>> Oh, my God.
>> How you doing, man?
>> Good.
>> What's going on, big guy?
>> Have you eaten anything?
>> Yeah, we had rice.
We got a fire.
We slept outside.
And it's just this giant dune
that comes out of the middle of
nowhere.
>> So how did you both look for
the idol at the same time?
>> There's two urns...
>> Uh-huh.
>> You each get to pick an urn,
and mine was empty and hers
had a clue.
And I was setting up camp.
She went back up, came back
down, but she never really said
if she got it or not.
>> You didn't charm the
clue out of her?
>> I don't know; she is clearly
on the outs with her tribe.
>> Really?
>> You think?
>> Yeah, that's what she said.
The idol is actually under
everybody's nose in camp.
I don't want to let that out of
the bag yet.
It's one very general clue,
and that's too broad.
So you know, I'll be patient
and just hope the clues keep
falling into my lap.
>> Who's that somebody going to
be?
>> Oh, yeah.
Like, he's a big guy, and he
looks like he's in good shape,
but I just haven't seen it yet.
>> But, I mean, I don't know
how soon we can do it.
I don't know if this Council,
it might be too soon.
>> Yeah.
>> I think if we just stay
chilled and let him keep
digging his hole.
>> Yeah.
>> So then the sad part is
somebody has to go.
>> Yeah.
>> Everyone has their strengths
and their weaknesses.
We just need to do what makes
the team stronger.
>> You're right about that.
>> What do you think, Coach?
>> The original plan when we
walked into camp was to go with
Sierra.
>> Okay, got it.
I didn't know how original
we were talking.
I'm like, wait a minute.
Is there a new original plan?
>> We're going to Tribal
Council.
And the girls think
that everybody is voting for
Sierra, but for me, the obvious
choice is Candace.
She's just a cancer on the
tribe.
I've been looking forward to
this elimination.
I think it's good.
I think it's what we need.
So hopefully, Candace has her
bags packed because she's out of
here.
>> How about you?
>> Yeah, that...
She crossed my mind.
Sierra was on my mind at first.
>> Coach, he wants to get rid
of Candace.
You know, I didn't necessarily
think he was right.
In the challenge yesterday, as
hard as Sierra played, I think
that she's just too small for
something like that.
Every time I saw her, she was
trying her hardest, but
somebody was holding her down.
So I think there's going to be
some challenges that probably
would suit Candace better than
they would Sierra.
We need to keep the strongest,
happiest tribe we can.
>> Yeah.
>> I will not vote you off
tonight.
>> I feel like it's my time,
it's my time.
>> I'm going to tell you
something.
I make my living off of people
trusting me.
So you just have to be cool
and relax.
>> Coach told me I wasn't going
to get voted out, but I know
that my whole tribe, from the
beginning, wanted to vote me
off, so I'm freaking out a
little bit about that.
>> Stop worrying.
>> I'm not worrying.
>> You are worrying.
You can't say you're not
worrying.
I know you're worrying.
>> I am not comfortable at all.
I still have not found the
hidden immunity idol.
So, I'm still looking behind my
back.
>> That's a long time for
people to be rallying.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I don't know.
>> Okay, let's think about this.
You and I are both strong.
>> Yeah.
>> The guys have been talking
about voting Sierra off for
days.
>> Okay, I worry about the fact
that, like, if anybody strays a
little bit, like...
>> Listen, I'm going to tell you
right now.
It ain't you or me.
They know what we're worth.
As far as I know, it's Sierra
going home.
And if it's not, then there's
mad shadiness going on around
this tribe.
>> Yeah.
>> Everybody trying to figure
it out.
>> And this is just the
beginning.
>> I know it.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach the flame, dip it in,
and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council because, in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire,
you're still in the game.
When your fire's gone, so are
you.
Let's go back to the very
beginning.
Sierra, based on very little
information, you were voted out
of this tribe.
What was going through your
mind at that moment?
>> Um, a part of me wanted to
give up for a second.
It was written all over my face
that I was sick, so I
automatically looked weak from
the get-go.
So I think their vote was valid.
>> PROBST: Tyson, what was your
reaction to Sierra?
>> She kind of looked miserable
on the truck.
I didn't see her pull
anything off.
I didn't see her gather very
much.
She seemed to be struggling in
the heat and didn't seem very
happy, so...
>> PROBST: Candace, how much
time was spent talking about
Sierra and why everybody voted
for her?
>> Honestly, there was a little
bit of resentment because it was
such a difficult trek and she
was taking a helicopter ride.
And I think she really wasn't
that excited to be here or
wanted to be here as much as
everyone else.
>> PROBST: And what do you
think the vibe is on you,
overall?
>> I think I'm vibing with the
group, but it's like, you never
know.
I mean, sometimes I talk a
lot, and maybe that might be
misinterpreted.
We're all different.
It's hard to tell.
>> PROBST: Coach, do you think
anybody would tell you this
early in the game if you didn't
mesh?
>> At this point, you got to
go with your intuition.
And if you're clashing with
somebody, you've got to sense
that on your own because I guess
at this stage, nobody is going
to tell you that.
>> PROBST: Let's talk a little
about Exile Island.
Brendan, how was Exile?
>> Um, it wasn't exactly
luxurious by any means, but it
was a cool experience to go
check out and have a chance to
kind of go there with Taj and go
through the process of Exile.
>> PROBST: So, Coach, how
curious was everybody about
Brendan's stay on Exile?
>> Right off the bat, he said
there were two jars, and one of
them had a clue to look for the
idol and the other one didn't.
He didn't get the clue.
And that's somebody that I
respect and trust and I believe
100% when he tells me something.
>> PROBST: Jerry, are you
surprised how quickly trust is
a major issue in this game?
You barely know these people.
>> Jeff, yes, trust is a major
issue in this game.
Because if you can win the trust
of over half the tribe, then
you'll be here for a while.
But if you can't win the trust,
your time here is going to be
limited.
>> PROBST: Hard to make a vote
this early on?
>> It's really hard to make a
vote this early on.
I've bonded with this group of
individuals so closely, and
we've got to know each other
real, I mean, real well.
>> PROBST: Erinn, what are you
reacting to?
>> We can talk all day about
how much we all get along and
this, that and the other thing,
but we don't know these people.
We've known them for six days.
But I don't know if the person
I've bonded with is who you
really are.
I just think we need to be
careful.
>> I have to disagree with
Erinn.
We're not at the Holiday Inn.
We are out there surviving
together.
That trek that we went through,
to me that's how you really get
to know someone.
>> But I don't know that that's
how you get to trust someone.
>> Well, I've already built
trust.
I've built trust with several
people on this tribe.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Tyson, you're up.
>> You played a great physical
game, but nobody wants a snake
in the grass.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
All right.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Candace.
Sierra.
One vote Candace;
one vote Sierra.
Candace.
Two votes Candace;
one vote Sierra.
Candace.
That's three votes Candace;
one vote Sierra.
Candace.
Four votes Candace;
one vote Sierra.
Second person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins: Candace.
That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Candace, the tribe has spoken.
Well, your first Tribal
Council, your first blindside.
Congratulations.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
The tribes are hit hard.
>> Push it!
>> Let's go! Move!
(screaming)
>> PROBST: And Taj makes a
secret alliance.
>> We would have a four-way
alliance that nobody knows
about.
>> That nobody knows about.
>> Exactly.
>> They won't even know what's
coming.
(laughing)
>> I'm surprised.
I'm really pissed off.
I worked really hard.
I worked in the challenges.
I worked on camp.
And I did everything I could
to try to make Timbira stronger.
And I thought that that was the
goal.
But I guess this is more like
day camp.
In the long run, I was an asset
and they're going to need me.