>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Coach and Brendan struggled for
control of Timbira.
>> As much as I like leading,
everybody trusts you as being
the leader.
If Brendan got voted off, and I
was the leader, I think this
tribe would be better.
>> PROBST: And Tyson chose
sides.
>> PROBST: Launch.
Jalapao took a beating.
J.T. has lost a tooth.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: And they lost their
third immunity challenge in a
row.
Timbira wins immunity!
Brendan was saved from Tyson
and Coach.
At Jalapao, with Tribal Council
looming, and Taj and Stephen in
control of the hidden immunity
idol, Taj reached out to J.T.
>> Listen, I can't believe it's
the real immunity idol.
>> I know.
Honestly, I don't want you and
Stephen to go out prematurely.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
the three stuck together.
Sydney, the tribe has spoken.
Down four members to Timbira's
six, Jalapao became a desperate
tribe.
Ten are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> At Tribal Council, Sydney
was voted out.
It's bittersweet.
I felt bad that she had to go,
but one of us had to go, and I'm
glad it's not me.
>> After tonight's vote, I feel
like the odd man out.
Luckily, I wasn't, you know, the
one being voted out.
So, you get a little nervous.
You get a little concerned when
you see torch after torch
getting put out.
You know, it's not fun.
It's not fun to lose.
It's not fun to vote people
you like home.
>> Maybe it will change.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
(thunder crackling)
>> Do you see Coach out there?
>> Yeah.
>> He's meditating.
>> He's doing his morning
meditation.
>> We're almost at day 20.
Up till now, it's been about the
team.
So I've been trying to get
along, but the little annoying
things I've had to keep bottled
in.
I'm the kind of person that if I
see it, I want to say, I want to
nail it, get rid of it.
And I was, like, you know what?
I need to get centered.
I need to pray.
I need to meditate.
And I spent about ten minutes
out in the water just getting
refocused, and it was, like,
boom, and everything just
clicked.
You know?
This is about me now.
>> Oh, that feels so good.
>> We're so close to a merge.
Could be today, could be three
days.
So I've been pacifying
everybody and getting along with
the tribe.
>> Oh, my God!
That's awesome.
Coach has a new thing:
his morning meditation.
Just hanging out in the water.
A little bit of this going on
every morning.
If that's the thing that turned
you into Mr. Nice Guy around
camp, you do it every day.
I will take you down there, hold
your hand, push you in the
water, whatever needs to happen,
because I like New Coach.
>> What will today bring?
>> What do you mean by that?
>> Huh?
>> Competition?
>> No. You're like a totally
different person now.
>> Life is good.
>> My relationship with Coach
to me has been good the whole
time.
There's definitely been some
things he's done around camp
which are kind of annoying or
outside the box.
And I mean, he's always...
doing his hair, and we were
talking about it,
and it's like, "I kind of
started the samurai thing."
And I was, like, "Started the
samurai thing?"
Like, they've been doing it for,
like, thousand of years in
Japan, and Johnny Depp's been
doing it for, like, 20 years
here.
You didn't start anything.
>> It's like a knot.
>> I know.
Feel it.
>> Oh.
>> Feel how hot it is.
>> Yeah.
Oh, shoot.
Yeah.
>> It was all the way out here
yesterday, and now it's just
right there, so...
>> What got into it that made
it... got it infected?
>> A little bug?
>> A bug?
>> Like, a little, you know,
bacteria or parasite.
>> Phew!
The only thing that concerns me
about Joe right now is his leg.
His leg is very swollen and red
from the knee down.
It doesn't look good to me.
He swears that it's getting
better, but I don't know.
With these two eyes, they don't
look too good to me.
>> I'm gonna post up in the
hammock for a bit, man.
>> Joe has a... kind of a
bummed-up leg, and he's down and
out, and, you know, um, if there
is a merge, even if there isn't
a merge, we're still...
Jalapao is still down to four
members, and things are really
not looking our way.
So there's a lot at stake for
every one of us if we want a
shot in this game, and this is
definitely the biggest challenge
yet.
>> Well, did we get tree mail?
>> So...?
>> Let's read it.
>> Coach, your hair tie.
One for you.
>> I'll have this.
>> "Head to head, face to face,
here's another to get your heads
spinning.
Getting away from camp and a
feast is what you'll end up
winning."
>> "Here's another to get your
heads spinning."
>> Spinning.
>> "Here's another to get your
heads spinning.
Getting away from camp..."
>> BOTH: "And a feast."
>> "Is what you'll end up
winning?"
>> Oh!
Oh!
>> It could be a merge.
It could be a merge.
>> Oh!
>> Merge. It could be a merge.
>> I just want it to say,
"Let's go eat."
Whoever wins this challenge
today-- they apparently, get
this huge feast, and I get
excited when I hear anything
that starts with an "F."
(laughs)
>> Y'all, we got to win a feast.
>> I think it's a merge.
>> I think it's a reward
challenge.
>> Let's take bets.
I'll eat your parts of the feast
if it's a merge.
>> No. I'm not sharing mine.
>> No. Let's just win whatever
it is.
>> Whatever it is, we'll win.
>> I'm real hard on myself when
I lose.
I hate losing.
I'm a sore loser.
So, if it's a merge, ball game's
on.
That's the reason maybe I'm
kind of hoping it's a challenge.
I don't know if I'm ready yet,
but, uh, I feel like I got to
redeem myself.
It's really fixing to hit the
fan.
>> Oh, wow, dude!
(cheering)
>> There's candy!
>> Give me some water without
bugs in it!
>> J.T., you have a sultry
voice; you do the honors.
>> Let's hear it, big guy.
>> "Congratulations, tribes.
You have merged."
(all cheering)
"...Replace your old
buffs with the new.
>> I love the green.
>> "You must come up with a new
tribe name, design a new tribe
flag and begin the next phase of
your adventure.
You will all live at the old
Timbira camp.
>> All right!
>> "All of your personal reward
items will be at your new camp
when you arrive.
Good luck. Enjoy your feast."
>> Yeah!
(cheering)
>> Let's eat!
>> Pig out, man!
>> Our biggest hope was that
today was the merge feast.
Less the merge than the merge
feast.
Jalapao is freaking hungry.
>> Those are real good.
>> Those are real good!
>> I was going crazy!
>> Yeah, Tyson's kind of like
a girl.
>> A toast?
>> Yeah.
>> Here's to Survivor and all of
us for making it, trying our
hardest and the merge.
Hear, hear!
>> Hear, hear!
>> Clink, clink, clink!
>> The feast, man, was cool
because we're meeting new
people.
You know, it's like getting
a new girlfriend.
There's all kinds of things to
explore.
(screaming)
I just wish we could have
decimated the tribe a little
bit more.
We had them on the ropes.
They were going to go down and
I think we could have won the
rest of them.
But it's all good.
We're in control, baby.
We're in control.
We can be in control for the
rest of the way.
>> So, anybody got any
history, secrets, and stuff?
I don't have nothing.
I'm a poor cattle farmer.
>> And you're a rocket
scientist, though.
>> Yeah, I am a rocket
scientist.
>> What do y'all...
what do you do?
>> I'm a soccer coach, but also
a symphony conductor in
California.
>> Symphony instructor?
>> Conductor, I'm a maestro.
So I do... I have two jobs.
I fly back and forth between
the two.
I like J.T., man.
He's a warrior.
I'm looking forward to getting
to know him.
And Stephen, I mean, he's
obviously intelligent and as
long as... I mean, I look
forward to these individual
immunity challenges, especially
in the beginning when we've got
all the big horses and alpha
males together.
That's gonna be awesome.
>> We need a new tribe name,
you guys.
>> Anybody know Portuguese?
>> I looked up "Will to
Overcome" and that was dingus,
I guess, d-i-n-g-u-s.
>> In Portuguese?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know about dingus,
man; I mean, that sounds like
a good meaning, but dingus
sounds a little bit too crazy.
>> I can't hear Jeff saying,
"Come on in, Dingus."
>> I'm in!
>> I think it has a nice ring
to it.
>> Any other suggestions?
>> Forza.
F-o-r-z-a is like strength in
Portuguese.
>> Forza.
>> Forza, which means strength.
>> Easy to say.
It took us, like, three days to
get Jalapao down.
>> I know it's a touchy subject,
but if we don't want to talk
about it now, that's fine.
We're just shocked by the last
two votes.
>> Good.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you guys didn't come up
with the idea of who was going
home?
It was kind of just, like, off
the cuff?
>> It was so... it was so big.
I don't know.
It's hard to talk about 'cause
it was so big, you know?
>> I was sort of tiptoeing
around Sierra because you do
need to be discreet with how
much information you give out.
You know, these are your future
competitors, so you can't just
be giving away your entire tribe
dynamic.
>> You guys are all great
competitors, and it's been a lot
of fun, you know, competing
against you.
>> So are you guys.
>> And when you guys win, I
think we all appreciate, you
know, definitely how well you've
done.
>> Well, thanks.
>> I was really worried about
the merge because
traditionally, if you're
outnumbered four to six going
into a merge, you're sitting
ducks.
>> Y'all got some fishing holes.
>> You've got to catch us fish.
We have not eaten a fish yet.
>> Fish man right there.
>> I'm really worried about
the numbers.
I hope that there's a power
struggle in the old Timbira
and I can exploit that.
Going into this four on six,
that's not good odds.
>> Welcome to your new house.
>> Thanks.
>> Look at that umbrella.
Look at all the pots we got.
>> Awesome.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Let's put that tarp out, like
right away.
>> It's like a real fixer-upper.
>> Hey, guys.
It's raining.
Let's put the tarp up.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I'm soaking wet.
>> That tarp is only as big as
that one spot right there.
>> You know, we're walking into
the old Timbira camp, and first
of all, we come up to a little
dog house shelter, and I'm like,
"What is this?"
You know, I mean, I don't know
how it was still standing.
>> We should take this top off,
just start pulling everything
off and then just rebuild it.
Not rebuild necessarily the
bottom, but take the top off,
just pull it all off, and then
just start from scratch.
>> You guys, should we do a tour
and show everybody the back
beach and the front beach and
all that before... so they have
kind of a feeling of the camp?
>> Yeah.
>> We got a pot full of beans
out there that's about half
cooked.
>> Let's see the tour.
>> The Timbira people are
definitely running the show.
It's definitely intimidating to
go into the merge down in
numbers.
They can pick us off if they
want, you know.
We're dependent on their good
graces.
So, even if we make allies with
them, those allies are in the
dominant position.
>> It's not near as big as you'd
think, is it?
You fish much?
>> Yeah, I do, uh... I do mainly
fly-fishing.
It's just, uh... I like the art
of... of the cast.
But, uh... I'm by no means an
expert.
(laughing)
>> You see them jumping at it?
>> I see.
I felt it as soon as I put it
in there, man.
I knew the first time that I...
that I looked at J.T.-- I saw
the cowboy boots, open, honest
face, and I said to myself,
"He is a good old boy."
We're kindred spirits.
We both love the outdoors.
I think that we're both
warriors.
Let's talk about the game a
little bit while we're fishing,
man.
How about it?
>> Man, I'm... I'm up for
anything, man.
It's not even 15 minutes, and
Coach is ready to talk about the
game.
And it was perfect.
I mean, I was... I couldn't wait
to talk to him about the game.
From what I know, Brendan
thinks he's in control of the
game pretty much.
>> Who told you that?
>> Taj.
I'm 95% sure he's got the idol.
>> So, you swear to me that Taj
does not have it.
>> I don't know if she's got it
or not.
If she does, there's two idols.
>> That's crazy.
All right, I'm going to tell
you a couple of things.
Um, when we talk, for now, let's
keep it confidential.
>> 100%, dude.
>> Just between you and I.
I said in the very beginning of
this game to everybody, I will
not lie one time on this game,
so let's just keep it honest
between us.
Let's keep it real.
>> I'll keep it real, Coach.
I've seen cracks right away.
I had some ideas before I
ever... before there ever was a
merge.
It's hard to keep six people
from different walks of life to
stick together when they hate
each other.
So, I'm just here to make sure
everybody hates each other.
If Brendan... if Brendan has got
that idol, we got... we're going
to have to blindside him.
>> I have a lot of emotions
going on.
I have said that I felt Brendan
was maybe a little bit
squirrelly, but if you flat out
lied to me, you better be
prepared to go to war.
I talked to J.T.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And the reason why I did is
because I told you in the very
beginning, you know, that he and
I had, like, this rapport...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...without talking.
I know him; he's a good old boy.
Well, check this out.
Brendan has the idol.
>> I thought so.
>> I want you to think about an
alliance with Stephen and J.T.
>> Here's what we do.
Me, you, J.T., Stephen, Debbie.
We keep that five, we can take
it.
>> It's time to go for the
jugular.
Brendan is the head of the
dragon.
When you want to defeat the
army, you cut off the head of
the dragon.
For him to go out as the first
person from the merge...
Mm, yes, I love it.
I mean, that's awesome.
>> Oh, good.
All right.
We've definitely found inroads
into Timbira.
This is clearly a very fractured
tribe because there's no strong
bonds and sense of place, so
there's a lot of power dynamics
at play that are very easy to
exploit.
>> Yeah.
(laughing)
>> I want you to catch one.
>> Okay.
>> Just put it out as far as
it can reach.
>> Should I keep bringing it
out and...
>> No, you can leave it in
there.
Unless the... took it off
already.
>> I got one, dude.
>> Huh, pull it up.
Pull it in.
Oh, it's a little baby catfish.
Pull him all the way in.
Catfish-- let me tell ya, they
got little fins that are, they
supposedly poisonous.
>> Oh, really?
>> See, he's got little razors
on the back of them fins.
See, watch him close them down
on me.
>> I was hoping for a big one.
>> Ow. Look at this.
What kind of catfish is this?
>> (laughs) I don't know!
A dangerous one?
>> It is.
I'll put him back.
That little bastard.
...right there.
I expected to not get along
with Tyson at all.
We talked a lot of smack at
each other, pushed each other
around, and now, you know, when
you get on the same tribe and
you go for individual immunity,
you're still competing against
the guy, but you're living with
him.
It's a little different now.
Stephen's the only guy that I
can vouch for 100%.
You know, so...
>> And with me it's Coach, and
as far as...
>> That's what Coach told me.
Whatever y'all wanna do, I'm
with y'all.
>> 'Cause I was thinking of
getting rid of Brendan like,
since, like, two or three
eliminations ago.
>> He's gonna be surprised as
hell.
>> I'm one of the guys that...
>> I'd like to get rid of
Brendan.
He's the biggest threat.
He just seems like a sneaky
bastard, you know.
I can't look him in the eye
and believe a word he says.
You can look me in my sweet blue
eyes all day and I'll tell you
sweet nothings and you'll
believe all of them.
Debbie, you want to go, uh, grab
some firewood?
Do you think we need some?
>> Sure.
We'll go grab some of the
timber and logs, yeah.
>> I'll grab that log on that
back beach, at least.
>> After the two tribes merged,
I was thinking we're probably
safe, Stephen and myself,
because of the secret alliance
that we have between us and
Brendan and Sierra.
But they haven't even made any
signs or signals, so, it kind
of, it makes me think that
they're going to stick behind
their tribe right now.
I went into Exile with Brendan
three times.
>> What do you think is going
on?
>> I don't know.
I don't know.
I can't tell if he's still with
us or not.
I can't tell at all.
I just, I feel like he's not
doing the things that he was
saying he was going to do
before.
>> My Exile alliance with Taj,
Sierra, and Stephen is still
kind of laying low, which is
what I think it needs to do
because that alliance is only
effective once the numbers get
down to seven or eight.
And so, right now, Joe needs to
go, J.T. needs to go, and then
my Exile alliance can kind of
take charge if need be.
>> Coach talked with J.T.
last night really good.
>> Okay.
>> J.T.'s a straight shooter,
good guy.
>> Okay.
>> He said he trusted Stephen
with all his life.
>> Okay.
>> Here's the alliance now.
You, me, Coach, J.T., Stephen.
>> I like J.T. and Stephen both.
>> They're both...
>> Straight shooters.
>> Here he comes.
>> Okay.
>> Wood?
>> Do you think Joe?
>> Yeah, I think so.
What do you think?
>> That's what I thought.
I mean, he's injured, so he's
not going to be able to compete
at stuff, don't you think?
>> Um, yeah.
>> I was going to go grab that
log because it was easy, but...
and it burned long, but if not,
we'll just, where should we go?
Anywhere?
>> We don't have much time.
>> Yeah, we only need the little
stuff.
>> I talked with Brendan, and,
uh, I just wanted to kind of
let him feel like that I was
still on board with whatever
plan he had.
I do feel proud being a better
schemer than Brendan.
He's supposed to be this
big-league businessman who gets
businesses rolling, makes them
tons of money.
He's like putty in my hands.
I can mold this game however I
I want right now.
>> Okay, first of all, did you
find yours?
>> Found it?
>> Uh-huh?
>> I got to get back to camp.
(laughing)
>> Based on the clues from
Exile, I was able to figure out
that there were most likely two
idols, and Joe and I decided
that we were going to work
together and see if we can maybe
find both.
>> So, you don't know where it
is?
>> Oh, no, not at all.
>> I can't even trust you.
(giggling)
I don't know what you're doing.
It's a simple question.
I'm asking if you have the
immunity idol.
>> I don't have it.
We're here.
>> You know where it is?
You bend over.
>> Yeah.
>> Do this.
>> It's not there.
>> It's not there anymore.
>> The idol is not there.
>> Yeah.
There was a very specific
pocket where something should
have been on the back of that
tree mail post.
There's nothing in there.
So, we can assume that Brendan
or Sierra has the idol.
We'll vote them both out and,
uh, then we can actually play
the game for real.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How's everybody doing?
>> Awesome.
>> Great.
>> PROBST: J.T., what's the name
of the new tribe?
>> Forza.
>> PROBST: What's Forza mean?
>> I believe it means "strength"
in Portuguese.
>> PROBST: All right, Forza is
the new tribe name.
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yep.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first, Debra: I will
take tribal immunity back.
Tribal immunity, no more.
We're now in the individual
portion of the game.
This is what you covet.
A beautiful individual immunity
necklace.
If you're wearing this,
you're safe in this game.
Cannot be voted out.
If you don't have immunity,
you are vulnerable.
Today's challenge is very
simple.
Each of you will hold on to a
pole for as long as you can.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: When you fall off the
pole, you're out of the
challenge.
Last person left hanging on the
pole wins immunity, is safe at
least one more day in this game.
Losers, Tribal Council, where
one of you will be voted out.
Big stakes.
We'll draw for spots and get
started.
This challenge is officially on.
>> I love you, pole.
>> PROBST: Stephen struggling
early.
>> I've got a lot of limbs
here, Jeff.
>> More than the rest of us?
>> PROBST: Joe, now struggling.
>> I know.
Salvaged.
>> PROBST: Joe really
struggling.
Finds a new resting spot.
Stephen struggling to hang on.
Stephen is the first one out
of the challenge.
Take a spot on the bench.
Joe now, starting to slip down
his pole.
Joe struggling to hang on.
That wood raking against the
chest.
Joe is out of the challenge.
(frustrated yell)
>> PROBST: Wow, what is going on
with that?
>> Uh, it's infect...
My knee's infected, man.
It just... it won't go away.
>> PROBST: It doesn't look good.
>> No, it doesn't feel good.
>> PROBST: Taj now having a
little trouble.
Brendan slipping a little bit.
>> I hate this challenge.
>> This hurts.
>> PROBST: J.T. now having a
little movement.
Sierra has not budged.
Debra has not budged.
Coach and Tyson haven't budged.
>> Ooh, aah!
>> PROBST: Taj now struggling.
Brendan drops out of the
challenge.
Taj right behind Brendan.
And Erinn, three people out in
succession.
We are now down to five:
Sierra, Debra, J.T., Coach,
and Tyson.
All vying for that first
individual immunity.
The only way to make sure you
are safe tonight is to have
that necklace around your neck.
>> Sierra, you're doing awesome.
>> PROBST: J.T. struggling to
hang on.
J.T. drops out of the challenge.
We are now down to four.
>> All from old Timbira.
>> PROBST: So, Coach, does that
mean Timbira's still going
strong?
There's no merge?
>> We are going strong.
We're going strong, baby.
>> Dude, you did awesome.
>> PROBST: Coach inching his way
down the pole.
Coach is now out.
Sierra struggling for the first
time in this challenge.
>> Ow!
Oh, that hurt.
>> PROBST: Are you all right?
That was a hard landing, wow.
>> Good job, though.
>> PROBST: That post got every
part of your body on the way
down.
>> You can do it, little Debbie!
>> PROBST: We are now down to
two people left in this
challenge:
Debra and Tyson.
Sometimes it is the simplest
challenges that prove the most
trying.
>> Okay, this really is
starting to suck.
>> PROBST: Debra now struggling
a little bit.
Tyson hanging on by a couple of
toes.
>> Tyson, you be careful you
don't fall off.
>> Don't boss me around, lady.
>> I just don't want you to
break your pretty little face.
>> That's true.
It is my money maker.
>> I know.
(laughing)
>> Don't make her laugh.
>> PROBST: Debra really
struggling.
She is the last thing keeping
Tyson from immunity.
>> Debra!
>> Debra drops out of the
challenge.
Tyson wins first individual
immunity.
>> Nice job.
>> PROBST: Tyson, come on over.
>> Good job, Tyson.
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
Tyson's safe at tonight's
Tribal Council.
The rest of you, one of you
guys going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Joe, stay behind.
I want to have medical take a
look.
Everybody else head back to
camp.
Congrats.
>> Am I staying here?
>> PROBST: I just want to have
medical take a look at you.
Can we get medical to come in
and take a look at Joe?
>> It's real scary right now
because I'm having to trust
people I just met.
You know, what I gotta do is
just remain strong to what I
hope is a firm alliance.
You know, I really don't have
any other options.
I have to trust Coach and Tyson
right now.
And if I'm still here tomorrow,
I'm not worried about old
Timbira anymore.
>> Yeah, that, that hurt.
>> That's sore.
>> Yeah, that's sore.
>> PROBST: You feel it more?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: You're not sounding
optimistic, Lucy.
>> This is really swollen, so, I
have to make an assumption that
there's a bunch of pus under
there, um...
>> PROBST: I got a question,
too, at this point.
What's your take?
Are you... you still want to
stay in the game?
>> I want to stay in the game.
>> PROBST: Okay.
>> Yeah, I mean, I want you all
to tell me if you don't go home
right now, you're going to lose
the leg.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: What's at risk for
him right now?
What are you most concerned
about, Lucy?
>> Unfortunately, because this
infection is so close to the
bone, is that the infection
could actually enter your bone,
and that's a bad infection.
Um, the other risk is that the
infection goes to your blood,
and that's extremely dangerous.
In that regard, that can risk
death.
This won't heal itself tomorrow.
>> Very beautiful.
>> Right on the lips.
>> I love you.
>> I love you, too, sweetie.
Here, want to try it on?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, so, I kick ass, like I
always do, and, uh, if any
ladies want my phone number,
I guess, uh... ask.
(thunder rumbling)
>> Wowee.
Is it going to rain all
afternoon?
>> We immediately knew
something was up with Joe
because he hadn't come back
from the immunity challenge.
>> I hope Joe's okay.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> We're hoping we can take out
Brendan tonight.
But, honestly, I've known these
people for two days.
They're obviously crafty people.
That's why they're out here.
So, I don't trust anyone, but
you've got to go with your gut
sometimes in this game.
You gotta make desperate
moves sometimes in this game,
and I think this is one of them
for me.
>> Are your forearms all
jacked up?
>> I only held with my fingers
and my toes the whole time.
Even coming down, I just
like...
>> You were probably smart to
not have shoes on.
>> When I climbed down a
little bit, like, it loosened me
up.
>> That's how I fell off,
when I went to stretch.
>> I kept trying to do that.
>> Mine kept falling out.
I couldn't get it to stay in.
>> Lying to everybody,
especially Brendan and Sierra,
actually brings me pleasure.
In my alliance now, Stephen and
J.T. have replaced Brendan and
Sierra.
I never liked Sierra ever.
I have no clue why she's out
here other than to just give
hope to stupid people around the
world.
>> Hey, it's the way it is, man.
>> I know, I know.
>> It's the way it is.
>> That's the way it is.
>> And Brendan, he's really the
sneakiest bastard I have to
worry about.
We smile at each other; we hug.
I've kissed him on the neck
softly.
He's felt my warm, steamy breath
on the nape of his neck, even on
the small of his back.
But, you know, as the old adage
goes, keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
That's right, right?
>> Here's the thing: if I go
with you, you know...
There's two basic alliances,
right.
I know I can get to the final
four with Taj and Brendan.
And I will go with you, with
Coach, Tyson, and Debbie now if
you promise me you will turn on
them when the time comes.
>> I will...
>> All right, we just want to
talk.
I just want to ask you guys.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, we're doing the beans
right now.
>> Right.
>> And then we're going to add
a little bit of rice to them.
>> Okay.
>> And then we'll, so, we'll
eat, we'll just split it up and
then in a couple of hours, we'll
split it up again.
Good?
>> That's cool.
>> Okay.
>> We're trying to get
everything straight.
>> If it's five, five, we gotta
stay...
>> I will get Erinn... I will
get Erinn to go to do this.
But she's not in on it still.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Got it.
>> What a mess.
>> We done with our awkward
conversations?
>> Yeah, man.
>> Get over here.
>> Is Joe back yet?
>> No.
>> Is it bad to fish in the
middle of the day in the rain?
>> It may be good to fish in
the rain.
You all want to try to eat some
fish before we go?
>> Yeah, we got plenty of time.
>> We got plenty of...
>> You guys want to go?
>> Not right now.
I'll meet you.
I'll come down there later.
>> I might come down in a bit,
too.
I like it down there.
>> All right.
>> There's definitely a
scenario where I could be in
trouble, within Timbira; my old
Timbira tribe senses something.
If it's going on with Stephen
and Taj and myself, they might
say, "Let's get rid of Brendan
now."
You know, who knows?
But so much of it is going to
be on the fly.
I'll have the immunity idol in
my pocket and I'm not afraid to
play it tonight.
>> I feel like Brendan and
Sierra haven't tried to really
communicate yet.
>> I know.
>> Tonight?
>> Yeah.
>> How?
>> I don't think that they're
unified.
I bet we could sway them.
I think we could sway like,
Coach, you know, Coach and J.T.
are seriously (indistinct)
right now, have you noticed
that?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Well, if you can pull it
together, I'll do it.
>> You will?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I know how tight you guys
are.
>> I mean, we're cool, but like
I said, we've been over here
for two days now, and I haven't
had the chance to talk to him,
and I don't trust him anymore.
I don't feel secure.
If we were even, it would
probably be different, but
because he has all the numbers,
it just doesn't feel good...
you know?
>> Taj, your teeth are
abnormally white, too.
>> So white.
>> I bleach mine, too.
>> I'm obsessed with my teeth.
>> I'm, yeah, I'm the same.
>> I knew it when we merged.
I said my last hope is to talk
to J.T.
>> You can trust me.
I know I can trust you, man.
>> And I know that.
>> Y'all just keep reassuring,
you know, me or Joe.
>> Well, it was perfect because
you guys went out and talked and
we were all in that circle, and
I'm not telling any lies.
>> Okay.
>> And they were going to vote
you, and you're the warrior,
and we're together now, man.
>> I'm on top of that, man.
>> All right, listen, just don't
burn me, okay.
>> I won't, man.
>> I just screwed my whole
tribe.
>> If I'm reading Coach right,
he's telling me the truth.
My life in this game is in his
hands tonight.
But, you know, this is a game
for a million dollars.
They're voting me tonight.
>> What?
>> Coach just said Sierra and
Brendan are the only two that's
going to vote me.
>> That means...
>> Hopefully, he won't play his
idol.
>> He's not going to play his
>> If he does, dude, I'm out.
>> You're not going out.
>> I was thinking, if, uh, and
Brendan's going to vote me.
>> Damn, it's 'cause Joe's
injured.
>> That's fine.
If Brendan's voting me and
Sierra's voting me...
>> We can split votes.
>> That's two.
This is awesome.
If Brendan plays the idol,
then it doesn't matter how many
of us vote for him.
One of the Jalapao tribe,
whoever he chooses, is going
home.
And it sounds like Brendan is
targeting J.T., which is
disastrous for me.
So, our solution is to split
the votes.
We have at least four or five
solid votes for Brendan.
The rest of us vote for Sierra.
That way, if Brendan does play
the idol, Sierra's going home,
and Brendan can go home next.
>> J.T. and I were talking about
splitting the vote just in case
he uses his idol.
So, four people, five people
vote for him, and two or three
vote for Sierra.
That way he can't vote J.T. out
no matter what.
>> That's true. That's true.
Let's do it.
>> Yeah.
>> We need to split the vote
now.
We need four on Brendan, three
on Sierra, and then Sierra and
Brendan's can go anywhere and
they don't count for anything.
So, whether an idol's played
or not.
You know?
>> I gotcha.
>> One of them goes.
>> At Tribal tonight, if it goes
the way that I planned it to, it
will absolute shake the hell
out of the foundations that
were Timbira.
>> Not a thing biting.
>> Really?
>> No.
>> Not a thing?
>> Nothing.
>> Not the time?
>> I have no patience for
sitting around holding a rod in
my hand without anything
working.
Did you catch that, Debbie?
>> I got it.
I heard it.
>> So what do you want to call
me?
You want to call me
The Orchestrator for
orchestrating a beautiful move
at this point in the game that
does two things?
Keeps my initial game plan
intact and I don't have
to compromise by keeping weak
people around, and voting out
one of the strongest, most
manipulative and possibly most
deceitful players to date.
Or do you want to call me
The Dragonslayer because I'm
cutting the head off of the
dragon?
You guys call me whatever you
want to because at this point
in time, I feel brilliant!
>> Is that Jeff?
>> It is.
>> Uh-oh.
>> Joe is gone.
>> No.
>> You know what, I'm going to
give him applause for not having
an umbrella.
All right.
>> PROBST: Ah, I missed you
guys.
>> You're not with Joe.
>> PROBST: No, Joe's not with
me.
Uh, have an update.
You guys left the challenge;
we kept Joe behind.
Medical really wanted to check
out his leg.
Everybody knows he's been
battling a pretty decent
infection.
They looked at it, did
a thorough assessment.
He can't continue.
>> What?!
>> PROBST: They said the risk of
him staying longer was too
serious.
>> Aw, jeez.
>> PROBST: That if they left him
longer in the game, that this
could get worse.
He didn't want to go.
He asked if he could stay.
He asked if he could stay
another day, but he couldn't
stay out here any longer.
So he's going to be evacuated
via helicopter.
He'll be taken to the nearest
city, get looked at
at a hospital.
They may do surgery; they're not
sure, but either way, he'll be
taken care of.
So the impact on you guys is
no Tribal Council.
>> Ooh!
I mean, I don't mean to sound
so happy.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Good news, bad news.
No Tribal Council for you guys.
Nobody getting voted out.
Nobody else going home.
>> Can you tell Joe that we love
him and miss him?
>> PROBST: Try to stay dry and
take care of yourselves.
And the game continues.
I'll see you soon.
>> Thanks for coming by.
>> PROBST: All right, guys, good
night.
>> Thanks, bye.
>> Brendan lives to see another
day.
I am disappointed.
The main thing about getting
the plan to work was keeping
everybody quiet for long enough
to vote him out so that he
didn't use an idol if he had it.
Now, I don't know how much is
going to leak or what's going
to happen, but...
>> I can't wait till the next
Tribal Council even more so now
because I have had some plans
in order and, uh, I think
someone on the old Timbira tribe
just bought themselves three
days, and they don't even know
it.
>> So, no Tribal tonight.
That sucks.
You know, I mean, it's like,
we've got a game plan.
I'm ready for action.
The Dragonslayer has to wait
another day to taste blood.
>> The doctor said that if I...
if it got bad, which it would
have if I would've stayed, that
I, you know, could potentially
lose my leg or lose my life.
This game is cool, but it's not
that cool.
I-I don't want...
I don't want to die.
I'd rather walk home.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: Brendan wages war
on Coach.
>> The Exile alliance
hibernated for a while.
It's finally going to rear its
ugly head.
>> PROBST: And Coach fights
back.
>> We're cutting the head off
the dragon.
When it comes head-to-head,
we'll see who really was the
chosen one.
>> The fact that you get
blindsided literally by your
own body just goes to show you
that this game is...
Anything can happen.
And I think that, like,
that's...
The main lesson I learned is
that generally speaking, like,
Mother Nature's pretty awesome
force, and this game is tough.
I don't know.
It sucks, man.