>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
>> I want you to think about the
alliance with Stephen and J.T.
I have the power alliance.
Commanding my officers like I
was born to do-- hence my name,
the Dragonslayer.
Sierra's going tonight,
no-brainer.
>> You're gonna be the next to
go.
You're not gonna be able to
change that.
>> Given another chance, I would
prove I am a loyal person.
>> Am I gonna give you a second
chance?
Probably not.
>> There's a large part of me
that prays for a miracle.
>> PROBST: Ninth person voted
out and the second member of our
jury:
Tyson.
Another Tribal Council,
another blindside.
This is shaping up to be a
battle to the end.
Seven are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> You rock, Sierra.
That was a big one.
>> I thought I was going home.
I totally thought I was going
home.
It's crazy.
I couldn't have asked for a
better Tribal.
>> Coach, I don't want you
or Debbie to feel like you were
out of the loop.
I knew you would not want to go
against your word with Tyson.
>> Right.
>> The reason that we didn't
tell Debbie and Coach that we
were gonna vote out Tyson is
'cause we didn't want them
scrambling and changing their
plan.
We knew what their votes were
gonna be.
We could safely get rid of Tyson
without telling them.
>> It was a good move, guys.
And I'm glad... I appreciate you
not telling me.
>> Bold and brilliant tonight,
guys.
I mean, I've got really good
intuition, you know...
>> Yeah.
>> ...and I didn't see it
coming.
>> Yeah, but I don't want you to
be mad at me, Coach.
>> I'm not in the least.
I appreciate you guys not
telling me.
>> Both Coach and Debbie
realized that the dynamics of
the tribe had suddenly,
dramatically shifted, and they
were trying to curry favor with
us.
So basically anything we had
done was the greatest thing that
had ever been accomplished.
You know, "What a tremendous
blindside."
It worried me a little bit
because I would rather have an
honest blowout than have people
smiling saccharine smiles at me
and, you know, plotting
something else.
>> Absolutely no hard feelings.
>> Thanks, Coach.
>> Okay? I mean it. I mean it.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Yeah, okay.
I love you two to death, and
I'll be honest: I trust you
completely.
>> Where I am in this game right
now is, I'm recoiling to figure
out exactly what my next move
is.
Kind of like a snake.
Stephen, J.T., and I talked
about all of us being there
towards the end, but do you
believe them?
That's the question of the day.
It's dangerous with Stephen and
Taj and J.T. together, and if
we take out Sierra, and then
Erinn next, they have everything
in line with what they need.
Then they can take me out and
then you out.
I would have bet my life that
Tyson was still gonna be here
today.
There is not any downtime.
You've got to work your people.
Every move is critical now,
and the next two people
supposedly that are on the
chopping block are Erinn and
Sierra.
That takes Timbira down to two
immediately.
Now where do we go?
I am not gonna be happy going
out fifth.
And I'm not gonna be happy you
going out fourth.
You and me, Sierra, and Erinn?
>> Otherwise, we're taking out
all our people, and then you and
I are sitting ducks, with no
leverage.
If we could pull all of the
Timbira tribe members back
together, and get Sierra, Erinn,
Coach, and myself, we would
outnumber Jalapao-- Taj, Stephen
and J.T.-- and maybe be able to
gain control of this game again.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
>> OTHERS: Yep. Yes.
>> PROBST: Today we're gonna see
how in tune you are with the
rest of the tribe.
I have a series of questions.
You're each gonna answer these
questions in private.
I will then tally the results,
and then I'll explain the
challenge.
Take an answer board and a pen,
find a private spot.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: All right, I have
tallied the results.
You're now going to guess what
the group said.
Whose name came up the most
often?
This may differ from what you've
said individually.
We are looking now for the
consensus.
Each time you get one right, you
get to make one chop on another
tribe member's rope.
When your rope has been chopped
three times...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: ...you're out of the
challenge.
Last person left standing wins
reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> OTHERS: Yeah. Yes.
>> PROBST: The winner of today's
challenge will be taken to the
fervadora, which is a natural
spring unlike anything you've
experienced before.
You will understand what I mean
when you get there.
You'll also join a local family
for a home-cooked, traditional
Brazilian feast.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: The winner will also
send one person to Exile Island.
A lot at stake?
Worth playing for?
>> OTHERS: Yeah. Yes.
>> PROBST: Go ahead and pick up
your boards.
Here we go, first question.
"Who has not lived up to their
potential?"
Remember, you are guessing who
you think got the most votes.
Everybody reveal.
A lot of votes for Coach,
couple of votes for Sierra.
The person whose name came up
the most often to this question
was...
Coach.
Debbie got it right.
Erinn got it right.
Sierra got it right.
Coach got it right,
and Taj got it right.
All right, Erinn, you're up
first.
Take your shot.
First blood.
So many choices.
>> Erinn!
>> PROBST: Sierra with the first
hit on her rope.
Two more, and she is out.
Debbie, you're up.
>> What?!
>> PROBST: J.T. takes a hit.
He's got two left before he's
out of this challenge.
Taj, you're up.
>> Little Debbie, it's not
personal.
I just want to eat.
>> It's okay.
I still love you, Taj.
>> I love you, too.
>> PROBST: Coach, the man who
has not lived up to his
potential, now gets to take a
whack at somebody.
>> Oh, wow.
>> PROBST: Coach whacks Sierra.
Sierra takes her second hit in
this first round.
Sierra.
>> I was already going for you,
Coach.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: Coach takes his first
hit.
All right, end of round one.
Sierra, the only person down to
her last hit.
Next question: "Who would
squander the million dollars the
quickest?"
Who would waste this money
faster than anybody else?
Everybody reveal.
A lot of names came up.
The correct answer...
Sierra.
J.T. got it right.
Debbie got it right.
Erinn got it right.
All right, Debbie, you're up.
Erinn takes her first hit.
>> Sorry, Erinn.
>> PROBST: J.T., you're up.
>> Oh, J.T.!
>> PROBST: And with that, Sierra
is out of the challenge.
>> Everyone hacked my rope
first.
I think that a lot of people are
being hard on me because I
think a lot of people still want
me to go home.
And yeah, it hurts.
>> PROBST: Erinn, you're up.
Debbie takes her second hit.
She's down to just one hit left
on her rope.
Next question: "Who would never
survive on their own?"
Everybody reveal.
J.T. and Coach said Sierra.
Everybody else said Debbie,
including Debbie.
>> I would have no one to talk
to, Jeff.
>> PROBST: The correct answer
is... Debbie.
Stephen got it right.
Debbie got it right.
Erinn it right,
and Taj got it right.
Taj, you're up.
Coach takes his second hit.
Erinn.
Coach is out of the challenge.
Take a spot on the bench next to
Sierra.
Stephen.
>> Sorry.
>> It's okay, babe.
>> PROBST: Debbie, you're out of
this challenge, but Debbie got
it right, so, Debbie, take your
last licks.
>> Sorry, Erinn.
>> It's okay.
>> PROBST: Erinn takes her
second hit, and with that,
Debbie will take a spot on the
bench, joining Sierra and Coach.
We are now down to four.
Taj and Stephen with all three
hits left on their rope, J.T.
with two left, Erinn with only
one hit left.
Next question: "Who would you
trust with your life?"
>> Oh.
>> This is a gimme.
>> PROBST: Everybody reveal.
>> This is a gimme, my friend.
>> PROBST: Everybody says J.T.
Correct answer is J.T.
Everybody got it right.
>> I don't know why everyone
trusts me so much, but in this
game I'm not so trustworthy.
And it seems like people would
catch on to that.
It may be the accent or
something, I don't know.
>> PROBST: Taj, you're up first.
>> Raah!
>> PROBST: J.T. takes his second
hit.
All right, J.T., you're up.
>> Erinn, I'm sorry, baby.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: J.T. takes Erinn out
of this challenge, but Erinn got
it right, so Erinn gets one last
whack.
That retaliation knocks J.T.
out of the challenge.
Erinn takes a spot on the bench.
We are now down to two people
left in this challenge.
Stephen, you're up.
Wow. Some force behind that.
>> Get your butt over here.
>> It's on.
>> PROBST: Taj now down to two
hits left on her rope.
Steven has all three hits left
on his rope.
Next question.
Who is most likely to stab you
in the back?
>> Mmm.
>> PROBST: That is not an easy
question to answer.
Reveal.
Correct answer is... Sierra.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Taj, you're up.
(grunting)
>> No!
>> PROBST: Stephen takes his
first hit.
Stephen, take your hit.
(Taj gasps)
>> I feel it in my chest,
Stephen.
Taj now down to one hit left on
her rope.
If Stephen gets this right,
he wins reward.
Who would you least like to see
win this game?
>> God.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Reveal.
Stephen said Sierra.
Taj said Coach.
One of you got it right.
One of you got it wrong.
>> Oh, I hate that.
>> The correct answer was not
Coach.
The correct answer is Sierra.
Stephen wins this challenge.
Stephen, take your last chop.
And with this, Stephen wins
reward.
>> Yay, Steve-o!
>> Good job, Stephen!
>> PROBST: All right.
Before we get to the reward,
a not-so-pleasant task.
>> I don't want to do this.
>> PROBST: Who are you going to
send to Exile Island?
Not only will they not be a part
of the reward, they're not going
back to camp.
They're going by themselves to
Exile, which is no fun at all.
Erinn, I'm really sorry.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Erinn, Exile Island
again.
Erinn does not look happy.
>> I decided that Erinn should
go to Exile because my alliance
of J.T., Taj, and Erinn wants to
keep Exile under wraps.
We want the four of us to be the
only ones on Exile Island, just
in case a new idol pops up.
>> PROBST: All right, Stephen.
Choose one person to join you
on this reward.
>> It's got to be Taj.
>> PROBST: Taj going to be
joining Stephen.
You guys are going to the
fervadora.
You'll have some nice food,
get away from camp.
One more person can come with
you.
>> Stephen.
>> I made a promise to Jet
that I would take him, so I've
got to take him.
>> PROBST: J.T. going on reward
with Taj and Stephen.
>> You're a reward hog.
>> PROBST: All right.
Debbie, Sierra, Coach, I got
nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Stephen, J.T., and Taj,
grab your stuff.
Head out.
Have a good time.
>> Okay.
>> Good old Stephen won the
reward challenge today and then
he picked Taj and J.T., part of
his original tribe, so now, I'm
afraid that when push comes to
shove, that Stephen and J.T.
will stick with Taj, and I'm at
their mercy.
>> Stephen, myself, and Taj
arrive at reward at a Brazilian
farm.
>> Hola.
>> Hey, man.
>> Hey.
>> We were greeted by a father
and son and taken inside their
kitchen.
(kids singing)
>> Hola.
>> Come sit.
>> Have a seat.
>> Oh, my.
>> That looks delicious.
>> Oh, wow.
Very quickly, dishes started
getting piled up on the table.
There was a stew with some kind
of meat in it.
There were eggs that were the
freshest eggs I might have had
in my life.
There was vegetables, you know,
carrots and beets.
These were all native dishes of
the region, and it turns out the
local cuisine is pretty amazing.
>> Mmm.
>> Very good.
Thank you.
(thuds)
>> Oh, no.
(crying)
The little three-year-old--
she fell off the table and hit
her head.
I just went into mommy mode.
I ran over to her; I picked her
up, and I'm like, "Oh, it's
going to be okay."
I had to control my emotions
because looking at her, I saw my
son.
When they told me she was three
years old, I'm like,
"This is my baby.
This is my baby."
And I missed him so much at that
point, so when I picked her up,
I just held her tight and I just
imagined her being him.
But she definitely made me
realize how much I miss my
family, and I will never go away
this long ever again,
ever, ever, ever.
>> After the meal was over, a
couple of the kids escorted us
down to the fervadora, which
was this local spring.
>> Come on, Steve-o!
It smells kind of weird.
Whoa!
I could see the sand, but
there's no bottom.
Apparently, the water spring is
pushing the sand up, but my feet
didn't touch anything.
I was just kind of like a cork.
I was just kind of bobbing
there, being pushed up by water.
(laughing)
>> Whoa!
It's pushing my feet out of the
water...
>> That's so cool.
(laughing)
>> Let's have a power talk now.
>> I mean, our next move is
obviously Sierra, right?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Because Coach is really
secure around all of us.
>> I think so, you know...
Sierra's a strong physical
competitor, you know?
The only reason not to do Sierra
is that she could be on our side
long enough to take out Debbie.
Debbie is shrewd.
Let's not discount Debbie as a
real strategic player.
Sierra's a much more erratic
player than Debbie.
I would rather play with someone
whose motivations I can guess,
but right now is a good
opportunity to get rid of
Debbie, so it's something that
the four of us can seriously
consider.
And, you know, I don't know what
Erinn feel about Debbie.
>> Erinn's with us.
She just feels like none of them
care about her, so why should
she care about them?
>> Right.
>> As soon as I got here, I
checked the urn and big
surprise, a new clue to the same
spot where the idol isn't.
We have checked and checked and
checked tree mail and there
isn't one there, so obviously,
the idol is gone.
(thunder rumbles)
Help me, please.
It's hard to be out here when
the rest of my alliance is out
on a reward.
I could not get a fire started
before it started to rain and
that killed me.
I had no food, no water, no
warmth, no way to dry anything,
and I slept in constant pouring
rain.
This is the kind of thing that I
think could break a person
down.
Like, I really didn't think I
was tough enough to do this part
of it.
I am about as girly and prissy
as they come.
So, in my own personal tally of
things that I've done in my
life that I never thought I
would overcome, this is going to
be at the top of the list.
>> She may be mad enough now
that they've sent her to Exile.
Sierra, you would go with
whatever Coach decided, wouldn't
you?
>> I don't know right now.
>> Okay.
>> I thought you said you were
going to be loyal.
>> Then you wrote my name down
last night and you didn't save
me like I asked you to and they
did.
>> So, that's how it's going to
be?
You're next then, baby.
So, I'm going to ask you this
again, Sierra.
>> I don't have an answer.
>> No, I'm asking you this right
now.
Where's your loyalty right now?
If it's not with Deb and I...
>> I said I don't have an...
Right now, I'm standing on my
own.
>> Well, Coach and I know where
we are and so...
>> You guys are in some big
trouble right now.
You guys have two people.
>> Who?
>> You two.
>> You don't know who we have.
You have no idea who we have.
>> Okay, so it's J.T., Stephen,
Taj.
They're connected.
They're not going anywhere,
okay?
Erinn voted for Tyson last time
without telling you guys.
>> Sierra, you don't need to put
threats in our head that we're
in trouble.
>> I'm not giving you threats.
I'm giving you the facts.
>> Fine!
The facts in your brain.
We have all lived a life of hell
for 28 days and I'm not doing it
with you today.
So I'm done.
I'm done.
>> They... he asked me.
>> I'm done talking about it,
Sierra, with you.
>> I didn't even bring it up.
>> It is over with me today.
Period.
>> Coach and Debbie came to me
and they were like, "We need to
get our alliance back," and I
was like, "Last night, you guys
voted for me."
Like, "What makes you think I'm
just going to jump right back
in?"
And they freaked out.
Jalapao's brilliant.
They used me to get to Tyson.
So, someone's playing their game
right and I think I'd rather go
with the smart people.
>> I know.
I can't believe that she, uh...
is that stupid.
>> J.T. said to me, "It's you,
me, Stephen, and Coach in the
end."
>> And do you trust him to say
that?
>> I don't know.
>> You just let me work on J.T.
If he wants him and Stephen and
you and I to be in the final
four, we have nothing to worry
about.
A line was drawn in the sand
today.
Sierra has no loyalty in this
game and the old Timbira tribe
is not going to get back
together, so I need to get a
concrete answer from J.T. on who
he wants to be in the final four
and then I'll make my move.
>> This conversation has to be
between you and I.
I'm laying all my cards out.
>> All right.
>> So, my question to you is
this.
Are you cool with Sierra going
next?
>> Yeah.
>> Then Erinn?
>> Then Taj?
>> Yeah, okay.
>> And that leaves, you, me,
Stephen, and Debbie.
>> I think that's the way to go.
>> This morning, I had all these
things churning in my mind from
the other day.
I'm worried about how J.T. and
Stephen blindsided Tyson, so I
really wanted to talk to J.T.
So that just reconfirmed the
next vote, Sierra will be the
one to go.
Sierra said something about,
"Let's talk about getting
Timbira back."
And I said, "That's not going to
happen."
I don't want to get in bed with
a snake.
She's going to do whatever it
takes to get her farthest in the
game without any honor.
I don't trust Sierra, and the
sooner she's gone, I think, the
better.
J.T. was very receptive, and I
trust J.T., so all in all,
a very good day's work.
And I'm like, I'm gonna play
like, for me right now, and they
both went bananas.
>> So, Coach approached you, you
wanna...
>> They both came back.
They both came back and...
>> They were freaking out.
>> Yeah.
>> Sierra came to me and said
that both Coach and Debbie
explored the possibility of a
renewed Timbira alliance.
And my immediate thought was
complete panic.
I am very scared of a Timbira
resurgence.
Ultimately, we know that we're
gonna have to betray Debbie and
Coach, and to do that, we need
them on our side.
I would like to include you, you
know, but like, you could be
playing me right now.
>> Okay.
Like, look at me.
I don't want to play any more
games.
I'm, honestly, at this point
right now, the least of anyone
to worry.
>> All right.
Let's, let's head back so they
don't think we're talking too
much strategy.
>> There's the man!
Stephen, I love you, man.
Come have a seat.
Stephen, no, but...
>> I was thinking, like, Debbie
and Coach are gonna think, like,
well, there goes the Jalapao
members, you know, BFF forever.
I mean, I figured you guys would
come back and be like, "We need
to take those guys out."
>> And you know what?
Of course that's what everybody
talked about, but it didn't come
out of my mouth.
As soon as we got back here,
Debbie and Sierra said, "Do you
guys wanna talk about, you know,
the alliance and everything like
that?"
And I thought about it for like
15 seconds, then I said, "I
cannot do that to those guys."
There's gonna be no Timbira
alliance.
I don't like it; it makes me
sick to my stomach to think
about it.
>> Sierra on board with the
new Timbira alliance?
>> Sierra's on board for
whatever she can do, but, you
know, she's just a half-wit
floating on the breeze, not
really knowing where she's
going.
>> According to Sierra, Coach
and Debbie are plotting against
me and J.T., and Coach is saying
that Sierra can't be trusted
right now.
So, I can't get a real sense of
who is telling the truth,
which makes me suspicious of the
three of them.
Sierra told me that Coach and
Debbie said, "This is our only
chance.
We got the numbers now."
>> ...getting the old Timbira
back together.
>> I just, I don't know, man.
I don't know.
>> There's a lot of stories
being told, a lot of paranoia
setting in.
I don't know what's going on.
I've got a lot to think about
now.
>> Well, he may just be like one
pathological liar.
>> If he lies to me, all bets
are off.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> I think she's loyal to us.
>> I know.
>> Eventually.
Me too.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
I'll now bring in Erinn,
returning from Exile Island.
>> Love ya, Erinn!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
>> You okay?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Here's a sweater.
Put it on.
>> Oh, my God, that's awesome!
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, Debbie,
first things first.
Give up the necklace.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
each toss a grappling hook
attempting to retrieve a bag.
The first three people to
retrieve all three bags move on
to the final round.
For the final round, you must
navigate a ball through a table
maze.
The ball falls in a hole, start
over.
First person to get their ball
into the finish net wins
immunity, guaranteed a
one-in-six shot at winning this
game and the million dollars
that goes with it.
Make sense?
We'll get started.
All right, first three to get
all three bags move on to the
final round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Coach misses his bag.
Sierra just misses hers.
Debbie with a nice toss.
That one might work if she can
get it over.
Just misses.
J.T. snags his first bag.
>> Ooh!
>> PROBST: Taj now with her
first bag.
>> Debbie and her first bag!
>> PROBST: Debbie with her first
bag!
(chuckles)
Stephen has one bag.
Coach snags his first bag.
Sierra's now on the board.
Erinn, the only person without a
bag yet.
>> I haven't eaten in three
days!
>> PROBST: Coach now with his
second bag.
J.T. with a good toss.
Can he turn that into a snag?
Gonna have to get far left...
and he does!
J.T. now with his second bag.
He and Coach are neck and neck.
Coach and J.T. each need one
more bag to move on.
Coach has his final bag!
J.T. has his final bag!
Coach and J.T. moving on to the
next round.
Erinn has her first bag.
Everybody even with one bag
each.
There is one spot left.
Debbie with a nice toss.
Debbie snags her second bag.
Debbie needs one bag.
Everybody else needs two bags.
>> Oh!
>> Ah!
Come on!
>> PROBST: Sierra with a nice
toss.
Just misses.
>> (chuckles): I got a knot.
>> PROBST: Sierra struggling
with this challenge.
Stephen with a nice toss.
He's got his second bag.
Debbie and Stephen each have one
more bag to go.
Stephen with a nice toss.
Can he turn this into a snag?
(Debbie screaming)
>> PROBST: Debbie nails it!
First one to get their bag
across the line moves on.
>> No!
>> PROBST: Debbie, Coach, J.T.,
moving on to the final round!
>> This is gonna be fun.
>> PROBST: All right, final
round.
J.T., Coach, Debbie, survivors
ready?
Go.
Very simple task.
Get the ball from the start to
the finish.
First person to finish wins
immunity.
J.T. off to a quick start.
Coach right behind him.
J.T.'s gotta start again.
Coach now with a decent-sized
lead.
Coach being very cautious.
Debbie going backwards.
>> Jeff!
>> PROBST: That is my fault, I
know.
That cautious approach starting
to pay off for Coach.
J.T.'s starting to come on
strong now.
Debbie right in there.
Debbie starting over again.
J.T. right around the corner
from Coach now.
J.T. taking a little risk.
And with a big move, J.T.
catches Coach.
J.T. with another nice move,
passes Coach.
>> Oh!
>> You better believe it, baby!
Dragonslayer!
>> PROBST: Coach wins immunity!
>> Good job!
>> Good job, Coach.
>> PROBST: Coach, come on over.
You're on the board.
>> Yeah, finally.
>> PROBST: Coach is safe tonight
at Tribal Council after 30
days out here.
One of you going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> It sucked to watch Coach win
today.
At this point, it's probably
Debbie or me going home.
So, I'm gonna do everything I
can to get them to go after
Debbie.
>> That was a good win today.
I was proud for you.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
>> You know, the mental
concentration.
>> Yeah.
>> This is the first immunity
challenge that I have won.
I feel like it kind of justifies
my place here.
The meditation, the prayer, the
focusing technique, I was able
to lock it in and win immunity.
With J.T., Stephen, and Debbie,
I'm very secure in my place in
the game, but it is a good
safety blanket to have.
>> If you guys are in alliance
with Coach and Debbie, you need
to know that they tried to form
an alliance with me to try to
get the numbers back to get rid
of all y'all.
>> He told me you tried to get
it back together, and he wasn't
gonna do it.
>> They came to me.
>> All I have is your word that
he done that.
>> Well, I swear on the Holy
Bible that I'm the one
who's telling the truth.
Coach?
I'm gonna let my dirty laundry
out because, you know, I'm
gonna go out with a big bang if
you guys are gonna vote me out
tonight.
Do you guys want to play dirty?
>> You're really scrambling,
aren't you?
>> You lied, and I want you to
admit it.
>> I have not lied in this game,
nor will I.
First of all, does everybody
want to do this?
Because I don't think everybody
does.
>> Lay it on us.
I'm... I'm just listening.
>> 'Kay. Yesterday when we came
back here, Debbie said, "Do you
guys want to talk about if
there's a ex-Jalapao alignment,
right?
And if we should talk about an
alignment ourselves."
And at that point, you got in
Debbie's face; Debbie started
crying; and I said, "Sierra, I
do not want a Timbira alliance,"
and that's it.
>> I didn't talk about a Timbira
alliance.
You guys both came to me and
asked me for an alliance.
>> We did not ask you for an
alliance.
>> I asked where you stood.
>> And you said, do you think
Erinn will be upset enough from
Exile to bring her on to four to
get the numbers back.
Did you or did you guys not say
that?
Because I will walk out of this
game right now if you look me in
the eye and tell me that you
didn't say that.
>> Buh-bye.
>> You are such a liar!
>> Sierra, we talked about our
options in this game.
When did you become this angry?
That's not the person that I
know.
>> And you're not the person I
know anymore.
>> Okay, fine, fine, I'm done.
>> Come on.
Don't-don't... Come on.
Sierra went crazy.
She's pointing at me, calling
me a liar.
I am a 46-year-old professional
woman, and I cannot believe I'm
in a verbal combat with a
23-year-old over what I said or
didn't say.
Honestly, a lot of it I don't
even remember, but it wasn't
gonna change the vote on her,
at least in my mind.
Who knows what'll happen
tonight?
You never know at Tribal.
It could be me.
Nothing would surprise me.
>> I think Sierra just caught
Coach in a lie.
>> Yeah.
>> It sounds like they actually
approached her about "Let's take
out Jalapao," and she said no.
>> Yeah.
We definitely have the numbers
to take out Debbie.
Sierra did a service to me and
J.T. by exposing Coach's
half-truths and Debbie's
scheming.
I definitely think Debbie is a
savvy game player and she wants
to win.
She is willing to make devious
moves.
So to take her out early
might not be a bad idea.
>> Right.
The problem with keeping Sierra
is she's causing a lot of drama
around camp.
>> Who knows what Sierra will
say?
Who knows who she'll piss off?
So sending her home eliminates
one big, nutty variable.
I don't know what to do.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Brendan and Tyson, voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
So, J.T., only seven people
left, not a lot of places to
hide.
>> Yeah, the game's definitely
changed, Jeff.
I mean, used to chitchat and
have a good time.
Now, I mean, I'm scared to go
fishing.
I'm afraid of what's going on at
camp.
>> PROBST: Debbie, is that true?
Are you starting to feel the
pressure of only seven people
left?
>> Oh, absolutely.
Our happy little family is not
such a happy little family
anymore.
And honestly, all this craziness
going on is a part of this game
I do not enjoy.
>> PROBST: Coach, has the
pressure been ramped up a little
bit?
>> I think there's been a
catalyst, so that we're
definitely reassuring ourselves
with people that we trust.
But I'm standing firm in what
I'm gonna do in this game, and
I'm not eliminating anybody
because I'm afraid that they're
gonna beat me later on in the
game.
>> PROBST: Sierra, a beautiful
eye-roll.
It went all the way around.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: What's going on
tonight?
>> Uh, Coach's profound claim to
being extremely honest kind of
got burned and ruined when Coach
and Debbie were just asking me
whether I wanted to be
Timbira-strong again, but I
basically told them they were
stuck up ... creek, and I
wasn't gonna help them.
And then, Coach decided to go to
J.T. and tell him that I came to
him and said these things, so
I'm happy knowing I just proved
someone was gonna "change the
game" in an honest way wrong.
>> PROBST: Coach, your jaw was
so tight while Sierra was
talking.
>> Obviously, my credibility is
being attacked by one person
because there's two things that
I am not, and that is a coward
and a liar.
And I honestly think that in
Sierra's warped mind that she
thinks that she's telling the
truth.
So she can try to make
accusations of two things that I
hold most precious: honesty,
integrity, and courage.
However, I forgive Sierra
because I really felt that verse
come to me where Stephen says in
the temple when he's being
stoned to death and his last
words are: "God forgive them,
for they know not what they do."
I was gonna come here tonight
and say, "Sierra, I'd like to
ask your apology."
Instead, she made enemies of her
two best friends here by
continuing to call us out
in front of our tribe.
Everybody up here now is sitting
here saying, "What the hell's
going on?"
So the catalyst that has
caused our tribe to distrust
each other is this girl that's
sitting in front of me, this
23-going-on-five today with her
temper tantrums.
>> PROBST: Taj, you're loving
this.
>> I absolutely love it.
I've been hearing it all day,
and it's, like, I haven't
watched soap operas in so long,
so this is really giving me a
boost.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: Debbie, let's talk
about other threats in this
game.
You won the last immunity
challenge.
You're clearly very popular with
everybody.
At what point does that become
a negative?
>> I hope that I'm not a threat
because I'm likeable, but I'm
still gonna be me, and I truly
liked everybody sitting here.
Like, it's gonna start getting
really hard for me to go up and
write any of these names down.
I don't like it.
>> PROBST: J.T., what's
important when you consider the
vote tonight?
>> You've got to factor in
physical threats; you got to
think about social threats; and
you got to start thinking about
people you want to take to the
end.
You've got to figure out how to
get rid of the rest of the
people without making them mad.
>> PROBST: And yet, Stephen, you
can't always vote somebody out
without making them mad because
if you start telling everybody
who you're voting out, you open
a doorway for them to scramble.
>> You're absolutely right.
I mean, you absolutely have to
blindside people sometimes, and
you know that there will be
repercussions.
You know, I'm sure Tyson doesn't
feel particularly warmly for the
people who voted against him,
but you have to balance your own
personal feelings against your
ultimate goals in the game, and
it's a really difficult decision
to make.
>> PROBST: Okay, it's time to
get to the vote.
Coach, you have the immunity
necklace.
As always, you can give it up to
somebody else or keep it for
yourself.
>> At this point, I think I'll
keep it for myself.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Stephen, you're up.
>> We've said it all.
There's nothing left to say.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay. Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Sierra.
Debbie.
One vote Sierra;
one vote Debbie.
Stephen.
One vote Sierra;
one vote Debbie;
one vote Stephen.
Sierra.
Two votes Sierra;
one vote Debbie;
one vote Stephen.
Debbie.
We're tied.
That's two votes Sierra;
two votes Debbie;
one vote Stephen.
Sierra.
That's three votes Sierra;
two votes Debbie;
one vote Stephen.
One vote left.
Tenth person voted out and the
third member of our jury:
Sierra.
Will you bring me your torch?
Sierra, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
♪ ♪
Well, it's clear the six of you
are struggling to trust each
other, and that means paranoia
is just around the corner.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Emotions run high.
>> Hey, babe, we miss you so
much down here at the George
household.
(sobbing)
>> PROBST: And Debbie turns on
Coach.
>> If Coach went next, I mean...
>> I started off super-sick.
I had the flu, but I persevered
through it, and I've done all
that I could do to stay in the
game as long as I possibly
could.
Coach was lying.
I guess they have to find that
out on their own. I'm just
totally floored that I made it
30 days, living essentially
in a bush with nothing