>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
(cheering)
The Jalapao tribe was bonding.
>> Get you some, man.
>> Wow, so good, so good.
>> PROBST: While Timbira began
to splinter.
>> I'm telling you, it's not
going to be perfect.
>> That's what I think.
>> You're taking out some
frustration.
>> No, you're taking out
>> PROBST: When Timbira lost
the immunity challenge, the
Survivors discovered a new
twist.
Brendan, choose one member of
the winning tribe to join you
at Exile Island.
>> Taj.
>> PROBST: Taj from Jalapao
and Brendan from Timbira went
to Exile Island and agreed to
work together, despite being
on different tribes.
They shared a clue to new
hidden immunity idols.
>> "Then tribal homelands is the
thing that you seek."
>> Our homeland is where we
live.
>> PROBST: Timbira, facing
Tribal Council, turned their
sights on Sierra.
>> Okay, got it.
>> PROBST: But when Candace
turned on Coach...
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: ...he retaliated.
>> She got on me.
She's going to get on everybody.
The cancer will ruin the tribe.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Sierra was saved and Coach got
his way.
Candace, the tribe has spoken.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> The last thing in the world
I wanted to do was give Candace
any idea that I was voting for
her.
And, like, not knowing what
everybody else was doing, I was
like, oh, my God.
This could be the very last
nail in my own coffin.
>> Erinn, obviously didn't see
it coming for us voting Candace.
And then when she did, she's
trying to, she's trying to back
out really fast.
She's-she's kind of panicking.
>> You guys were pretty
attached at the hips the
last two days.
>> 'Cause I wasn't sure about
her.
>> But she was turning on the
rest of us.
>> Yeah.
>> And you...
>> But I did know though...
>> You knew that.
>> You knew she was turning on
the rest of us, right?
>> But, like, it just really
wasn't a decision that I wanted
to make lightly until I felt
like, felt like I knew her
pretty well.
And once I did, I just felt
like I could not trust her for
a second.
>> Not only did she align
herself with the wrong person--
Candace-- she's has completely
insulted all of our
intelligences when we came back
tonight and she said, "You
know, I've just been hanging
around with Candace the last
couple of days because I just
wanted to see what she was up
to because I didn't trust her."
>> We weren't not getting along.
I was very cautious with her.
But I wasn't like, "Okay, we're
best friends."
Well, it's all over with, so
that's good.
>> For her to say that to us is
insulting, which is why she
never would have been in my
alliance from the very
beginning.
And she's made her bed, and
she's going to have to lie in
it.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
(coughing)
>> It's like, why are we doing
this again?
I go, "Okay, a million dollars,
a million dollars."
>> Yeah.
(laughter)
>> Getting back from Tribal
Council was a little weird.
>> Morning.
>> Hi.
>> How you doing?
>> I think that the time that I
spent with Candace in the last
few days probably associated me
a little bit with her more than
I would have liked.
Now I have to turn girl that
maybe is kind of on the outs a
little bit into absolutely the
opposite of that.
>> Got to win this challenge
today, man.
We got to be absolute animals
today.
>> I think it's really
important that we win
challenges, so I have to go in
there and I have to outperform.
Do I think that I can outperform
Sierra and Debbie?
I think so.
I'm just going to have to
really, really suck it up and do
it because now I feel like I'm
kind of fighting for my life a
little bit.
>> Unfortunately, that's all
we've got for breakfast, Jerry.
Yeah, but you didn't eat
dinner, either.
>> Oh, my God, yeah.
>> Well, it maybe-maybe had been
what had my, uh, stomach screwed
up.
>> Ugh.
>> Yeah.
Best beans I ever had.
>> I'm not feeling too hot
these last couple days.
I don't know whether it's the
beans or something I've been
eating or something that's been
causing my stomach to hurt real
bad.
>> You're sure not digging in
like you usually do, buddy.
(chuckles)
>> Oh, he's taking it slow and
steady.
>> Yeah.
I'm used to some type of
situations like this when I was
in, uh, Afghanistan or
different-- other military
spots, so--
I never like to show weakness
anywhere I go.
I always want to be looked upon
as one of the stronger ones.
While everybody is doing their
normal activities, I got to
pretend that I'm happy, but
really inside, it's miserable.
(chuckles)
I'm-I'm trying to fight through
this.
I figure another day or so, I
should be good.
(groans)
>> How you feeling, Jerry?
>> Mother said there'd be days
like this.
>> Yeah.
(Jerry chuckles)
>> There are a bunch over here.
You want to move on this side?
>> Yeah, sure.
I see some over here.
>> There's a couple in there,
small ones.
>> There are a bunch of small
ones over here.
>> There's some right-right
under me.
>> Drop it.
He was right here.
Let's make sure.
>> We got fishing gear in the
challenge yesterday, and we were
all so psyched.
We assume... I think we all
imagined that we would be
feasting on plates of fish.
>> I see some over here.
>> There's a couple in there,
small ones.
>> There's a big one right here.
If we can get it over enough, we
can catch him.
>> Toss it far.
>> One, two, three.
You threw it on my head.
>> I'm sorry.
>> That might, it might be all
right.
>> No, he got out.
>> We're having a lot of
problems catching minnows.
We're not entirely sure how to
use the net.
J.T. thinks it's a throw net,
but it seems way too big for one
person to throw.
So we... I think we need to
figure out a good system.
>> One, two, three.
It's still not easy, but, you
know, we figured out, you know,
live bait with the minnows is
definitely the way to go.
This water is just a little
different from where I came
from, but we'll get it under
control.
>> Oh, baby, come on in.
>> You see him?
>> Got him.
>> Woo-hoo!
>> Attaboy.
>> All right.
Attaboy, J.
>> Think this may be first fish
I've ever caught.
>> Oh, it is.
Good.
>> Oh, oh!
I got one, buddy!
>> Oh, my God!
Whoa!
That is a fish.
Hello, dinner.
>> That's right.
>> My biggest fish yet.
>> I could eat.
>> Today is the first day I feel
really hungry.
>> Look at that.
>> That one looks delish.
>> Oh, my God.
It's like a feast.
Mmm.
>> It's amazing how it doesn't
need seasoning.
It just tastes well seasoned,
doesn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you, guys.
>> Did you eat that skin?
>> That fish tasted just like
victory.
Just knowing that we got a
little food, finally using the
fishing gear the way it should
be used, I think it means that
we're just a force to be
reckoned with right now.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Jalapao getting your first look
at the new Timbira.
Candace voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
For today's challenge, six
members of each tribe will be
blindfolded and tied together
in pairs.
The remaining tribe member will
guide you through a maze.
You'll locate your bucket, then
make your way to a water tower,
where you must fill your bucket,
then race back to the start and
empty the water into a
container, raising a flag.
You'll then repeat the process,
this time collecting corn from
another tower.
First tribe to fill both
containers, raising both flags,
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes, please!
>> PROBST: It starts with this
tarp.
>> Oh!
(shrieking)
>> PROBST: It includes an
umbrella, chairs, pillows,
blankets, and a hammock.
In addition, the winning tribe
will choose one member of the
losing tribe to go to Exile
Island, and that person will
select somebody from the winning
tribe to join them.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Give you a minute to
figure out who's gonna be
blindfolded, who's gonna be the
guide.
We'll get started.
The caller for Jalapao: Joe.
For Timbira: Debra.
Here we go, for reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> J.T., Sydney, go left.
Y'all start moving, Spencer.
>> Straight!
Straight!
>> PROBST: Take a lot of
teamwork to figure this out.
>> Straight, straight, straight!
>> J.T., start inching left.
>> PROBST: First thing you have
to do is find your buckets.
Each pair will have a bucket.
>> I got a bucket.
>> PROBST: J.T.'s got a bucket.
>> Right, right, right!
Faster!
Forward!
Forward, forward, forward!
>> PROBST: Sierra's got a
bucket.
>> Get on that rail!
Go right! Go right!
>> PROBST: Taj has got a bucket.
Spencer's got a bucket.
Jalapao has their buckets.
Now you got to start collecting
water.
>> Spencer, water's to your
right!
>> Water's on your right, right!
>> Step straight!
It is on your right!
>> PROBST: Tyson has his bucket.
>> Keep going! Keep going!
>> Here, here, here.
Put the bucket right here.
Stephen getting some water for
Jalapao.
>> Where's the water?
>> Straight!
Right, right, right!
You're there!
You've got it, girls.
Okay, go!
>> PROBST: Sierra and Erinn
getting a little water for
Timbira.
Spencer and Stephen heading
back with water for Jalapao.
>> Spencer, you're doing great,
bubba.
Keep coming straight.
Slow down.
Oh, no! My bad!
All right, to your left.
>> We need to go back and get
our buckets.
>> PROBST: Taj now has water,
heading back for Jalapao.
>> Brendan!
Where is our bucket?
>> Brendan, go out straight to
your left, to your left!
Left! Left! Left! Left!
>> PROBST: Brendan and Jerry
doing their own thing.
>> Okay, Spencer, keep coming.
You're right on the holster.
You feel the pegs?
>> Here, here, here.
>> Okay, now pour.
Good job, guys.
Go!
>> All right, let's go back.
>> Back up, back up.
Come back towards me!
>> Brendan, no!
That's not ours!
Around the other side!
>> PROBST: Brendan still trying
to find his bucket.
Timbira in trouble early.
>> Left!
>> Come on, baby, let me get it.
>> PROBST: Jalapao, empties
their second bucket.
>> Stop, stop!
Get down behind you.
By your butt, by your butt,
by your butt.
>> Okay, I got it, I got it.
>> PROBST: Brendan and Jerry
finally get their bucket.
Timbira falling way behind.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> J.T. and Sydney head back
with water for Jalapao.
J.T. to your left, bro.
To your left.
>> Tyson is going to lead.
You guys follow me.
>> Let's go, Tyson.
>> Come on, Tyson, walk!
No, not yet. Not yet.
Okay, J.T., pour.
That's good.
>> PROBST: Jalapao has three
buckets in.
Timbira has yet to dump any
water.
>> Okay, go, go, go!
>> Okay, now we're ready.
>> Straight, straight, Tyson!
>> PROBST: Tyson leading one
long Timbira trail.
Timbira is in slow motion in
this challenge.
>> Come left! Come left!
Left, left!
You'll feel Stephen.
>> Tyson, stop, stop!
Left!
Follow it to the end.
Come straight.
There it is.
Forward!
There you go.
>> That's the water?
>> That's water.
>> This ours?
>> PROBST: Timbira starts
dumping their water.
>> It's right in front of you.
Keep coming straight.
Yes, yes, yes!
Pour!
>> PROBST: Stephen pouring.
Will this be enough water?
It is.
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Jalapao now looking
for corn.
Timbira still pouring their
water, trying to raise that
flag.
>> Dump it.
Okay!
>> PROBST: Timbira very close on
the water, but they're going to
need a little more.
They got to go all the way back.
>> J.T., to your left!
>> PROBST: J.T. has the corn.
He's filling his barrel...
and his face.
>> Go straight, straight!
>> PROBST: Jalapao's entire
tribe is at the corn tower.
Timbira still needs a little
water.
>> Right, right!
Right! Right!
Right there!
Forward!
>> To your right, J.T.
To your right, J.T.
>> PROBST: Jalapao has worked
well together from the start.
Spencer and Stephen now heading
back.
>> Debbie, do we need all three
buckets of water?!
>> Just start coming!
I don't know!
I can't see it!
PROBST: J.T. and Sydney dumping
that first bucket of corn.
>> Nobody's holding me.
>> I don't know where everybody
is.
>> PROBST: Timbira, really
blowing this challenge.
>> Come on, Timbira.
>> Spencer, put your right
hand down.
The trough is right there.
>> This is it.
This is it.
>> You got to bring more at a
time!
>> Where is it? Where is it?
I got it.
>> That's good. That's good.
>> PROBST: That's it!
(cheering)
Jalapao wins reward!
>> Oh, my God.
I love you guys.
(screaming angrily)
>> Way to go, Joe.
(groaning)
>> PROBST: Jalapao,
congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: First decision you
have to make, who from Timbira
are you going to send to Exile
Island?
>> Brendan.
>> PROBST: Brendan once again
going to Exile.
>> PROBST: All right,
Brendan, who from Jalapao do you
want to join you at Exile?
>> Taj.
>> PROBST: Same pair going back
again.
Spencer, does that concern you
at all that the same two people
are going back yet again, have
time together?
>> It seems like both tribes
are using the same strategy, so
I'm not entirely shocked.
>> PROBST: Brendan, your map,
not that you need it.
Head down to the beach.
>> Bye, baby.
>> PROBST: You'll both be back
in time for the next immunity
challenge.
Jalapao, grab your stuff.
Head out.
You've got a lot it carry.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: Camp life at Jalapao
just got a whole lot better.
Sadly, Timbira, I got nothing
for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> We've got to turn it around,
just for every reason
imaginable: pride, the rewards,
the anger that I'm feeling.
Winners find a way to win.
Losers find a way to lose.
We've got it get it together.
(thunder rumbles)
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, I know it.
>> I think we need to have a
little talk later.
>> What happened?
>> No, it wasn't.
>> I let out a scream at the
end of the challenge, a primal
yell that was about a quarter
of what I felt inside because I
was just so...
I was so pissed off.
>> If we give in right now to
it, it's...
>> Give in?
We're not giving in.
>> I mean, just like, give in to
the anger or the upsetness.
>> I was totally embarrassed.
I mean, there's no other word
for it.
We were humiliated.
>> Now, my biggest thing is I
just feel like I've let
everybody down.
>> I mean...
>> Sierra said you guys couldn't
hear me.
And I was screaming at the top
of my lungs.
Maybe that was the problem.
I was screaming instead of...
>> It's not like we're not all
trying.
>> No, not at all.
>> There's nothing about trying.
I mean, the last that thing we
should do...
And I beg all of you to not go
off in groups and say, "Man,
you know, Erinn really screwed
up today or Debbie really
screwed up today," because that
would be the worst thing we
could do.
>> So, what are you thinking?
>> People are just panicked in
the challenges.
Did you see...
Have you seen Sierra?
>> Yeah.
>> She screams.
She's like, "Aah! I can't hear!
Aah!"
Every time.
I'm just like, "Oh, my goodness.
I mean, who's worse?
Is it Erinn?
Is it, you know, Sierra?
I mean, obviously, I want to get
Erinn out immediately.
>> One word to describe Coach?
I think that's it.
"Coach."
You know?
He's not always the best at what
he's coaching, but he thinks he
knows the most.
>> I mean you, me, Sierra, and
Debbie are going to vote Erinn
off next.
It doesn't matter what Brendan
thinks.
I'm sure he'll be with us
because that's four to three.
>> He likes his voice to be
heard, which is what we all want
and all need.
>> And we only just see things.
We don't even have to talk.
And I think that's going to
be...
But as we're getting to know
each other, you know...
>> Yeah.
>> The first seven days, I
wanted to make sure you saw it
the exact same way as I did.
(laughing)
>> You know what?
When he told me I was like his
assistant coach, more power to
me, you know?
>> Cool.
>> Thank you.
>> Yup, sweet.
I'm glad we're seeing it exactly
the same.
I love it.
>> But he has a little
schoolboy crush on me.
People see that.
He loves me, you know.
So, if I just keep plugging
away, I'll eventually make
coach.
He may promote me.
I don't know if I'll have my
own team or will be co-coach,
or whatever.
But people are going to start
calling me that.
I'm actually going to demand it.
If we ever get put on separate
tribes in this game, I will
demand that the other tribe
calls me "Coach," too.
>> On three.
One, two, three!
>> Pao!
>> All right.
>> Oh, my God.
>> We did great.
I mean, we did.
>> That was awesome.
>> It was like organized chaos.
>> You did phenomenal.
Slow and methodical.
>> We won.
We won the reward challenge
today.
It was awesome.
We work very, very well
together.
>> Coach was pissed.
"I'm pissed!"
>> Hey, if we get this next
immunity challenge today,
we're sweeping.
Timbira's got to be struggling
right now with morale.
I mean, I think we put it to
them pretty good today.
I mean, we could really do some
damage if we won the next
challenge.
>> Hey, can we get somebody
else back here to help lift
this up?
>> We got to run it back here,
too.
>> It's got to come back my way.
>> Back this way.
>> It makes a huge difference
to have a tarp because we know
it's hard to make a roof rain
proof at this point, and I know
they're getting soaked and
we're staying dry and that's
going to make a big difference
on the next challenge.
>> To say...
To say something about the fact
that not only are they taking
those pillows and blankets, they
took my other blanket and
brought it to Exile.
(thunder rumbles)
>> Judging on the fact that
Jalapao seems to be a hell of a
lot dirtier than us, they
probably need that stuff more
than we do.
I don't care about comfort.
No shelter.
Let me bury myself in the sand,
get eaten by tarantulas and
bitten by snakes.
I don't care about comfort
anymore.
I don't want care about
anything else except for winning
this game.
>> You must choose...
Each choose an urn.
Oh, damn.
>> Is it empty?
I keep doing the same thing.
Oh, no.
I got it this time.
Open in private.
All right.
I'll be back in two seconds.
>> Okay.
>> Clue Two.
"You must search around.
You can and you should.
The item desired is surround by
wood."
>> Uh-oh.
(Taj laughs)
>> What do we got?
>> It's back home.
It's surrounded by wood.
>> We got another clue.
We got another clue.
>> Oh, perfect.
Perfect!
>> Oh, good.
Brendan and I back in Exile
Island.
He's kind of working right
along with me.
We both have the same goals in
mind in that we're trying to
find the idol so we can both be
safe in the long run.
So, then, we have at least three
days...
Or two days after we get back
from Exile to find it on our
own.
>> When I get back to camp, I'm
going to look for the idol
immediately and the first place
I'm going to look is something
that's surrounded by wood.
When I hear, "surrounded by
wood," I think of my shelter.
I think of the tree mail area.
So that's probably where I'll
take a peek.
The key is getting the immunity
idol.
>> I know.
If we don't find it by the time
somebody else gets here and gets
a clue, then we're outed.
Unless we can convince them to
send us again.
>> God...
Hopefully, we can and we'll
work on that.
>> Right.
>> But if we can't, who else do
we send?
>> Steve.
Do Steve and I'll prep him
before the next challenge, so
he'll know.
>> Okay.
So then, like, I'll go to
Sierra.
>> Are you sure you can trust
Sierra?
>> Yeah, I think I can.
>> Okay.
>> I'll make sure.
>> You work Sierra.
I'll work Steve.
>> Yeah.
>> Once we make it to the
merge, we would have a four-way
alliance that nobody knows
about.
>> That nobody knows about.
>> Exactly.
If Brendan and I can line up
our cards exactly the way we
want them, we'll have a secret
four-way alliance that no one
knows about.
This is going to slap them
behind the head and they won't
even know it was coming.
>> You're the best accomplice
ever.
Ever!
(laughing)
(thunder rumbling)
♪ ♪
>> Overall, though, I was happy
that it rained.
I knew they were getting wet.
>> Oh, my God, except for T.G.
>> Yeah, I try not to think
about T.G.
(indistinct talking)
>> Yeah.
>> You all right?
>> I'm great.
Last night was cold and raining
and miserable.
But for Jalapao, it was awesome.
We had the best sleep of our
lives.
We had our blankets, we had our
new shelter, and we had the
knowledge that Timbira was
having a miserable night.
So that made us all sleep pretty
soundly.
>> Oh, dear. Oh, boy.
(laughing)
You know, Jalapao is looking
great.
I hope Timbira doesn't have it
together 'cause if we got 'em
on their heels, now is the time
to put 'em down, and that's what
I'm hoping for.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
Brendan and Taj returning from
Exile Island.
>> What's going on?
>> Welcome back, T.G.
>> (laughs)
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> OTHERS: Yeah!
>> PROBST: First things first.
Sandy, I will take it back.
>> Okay.
Bye.
We'll see you soon.
>> We don't think so.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Let's get to it.
For today's challenge, two
members of each tribe will race
to roll a large, tri-colored
crate back to your mat.
Once you've gathered all six
crates, you must stack them to
build a staircase that spells
out your tribe name.
First tribe to correctly stack
the crates and get all their
tribe members to the top of the
tower wins immunity.
Losers, Tribal Council, somebody
going home.
Big enough stakes?
>> OTHERS: Yeah. Yes.
>> PROBST: Give you a minute to
strategize; we'll get started.
First pair for Jalapao: J.T. and
Taj.
For Timbira: Brendan, Debra.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, guys, come on!
>> Go, guys!
>> Come on, guys!
>> Let's go, T.G.!
>> Good job, Brendan, Debbie.
Let's go, you guys got it.
>> Yeah! Come on, guys!
You got it!
>> Good job, y'all!
Straighten it out.
>> PROBST: J.T. and Taj doing a
nice job.
They'll be back first.
Stephen and Sydney out on the
course for Jalapao.
Sierra and Tyson out on the
course for Timbira.
>> (indistinct shout)
>> Come on, guys!
>> Come on, Sierra!
(indistinct shouts)
>> Come on, you guys!
>> Come on, Stephen!
>> Keep it straight!
>> PROBST: Tyson and Sierra
making up a lot of time for
Timbira.
Next two out for Timbira: Erinn
and Coach.
Stephen and Sydney have lost a
lot of time on this round.
Joe and Sandy out on the course
for Jalapao.
>> Get it started, Joe!
>> We're still ahead, you guys!
>> Come on, guys, go, go, go!
>> Come on, Erinn!
>> Come on, Coach!
>> PROBST: Brendan and Jerry now
out on the course.
J.T. and Spencer now out on the
course.
Both tribes have three crates
left.
>> Come on, guys! You got it!
>> PROBST: Jerry gets hit.
>> Come on, Jerry!
>> (speaking indistinctly)
>> PROBST: Brendan and Jerry
back for Timbira.
Jerry's hurting.
>> Come on, guys!
>> PROBST: J.T. and Spencer.
Joe and Stephen out on the
course.
>> Come on, boys! You got it!
>> PROBST: Timbira back with
their fifth block.
Tyson and Brendan back out on
the course.
Spencer and Taj going out for
their final crate.
Timbira with a big lead.
>> (indistinct shout)
>> Come straight this way!
Keep it straight!
>> PROBST: Spencer and Taj still
fighting.
Brendan and Tyson back for that
final crate.
Start working on it.
>> This will be our bottom
block, you guys.
That's right. That's right.
>> PROBST: Keep digging.
Get it over there.
Jalapao's back.
Start working on it.
>> I think this is gonna be the
first step right here.
>> Push.
>> PROBST: You're building a
staircase that will spell out
your tribe name.
>> Right here. This is it. Okay.
>> All right. Now this one.
>> This one, it's this one.
It's this one; it goes there.
>> PROBST: Erinn is leading her
tribe.
>> And then that means that you
have half an "A" on that side.
That's right. That's right.
>> PROBST: Giving Timbira a big
lead.
>> ...two, three, lift. Go.
>> PROBST: Everybody working
together on Jalapao, still
staying in there.
>> Now twist it around.
(indistinct talking)
>> There's "R-A" right here.
>> All right.
>> This is not a diagonal,
though.
This is the top block.
>> No, this is gonna be the side
over there.
>> No.
>> Are you sure?
>> "T-I" is right here.
>> Come here, look.
T-I-M-B-I...
The "A" is gonna be up top here.
>> So is that it right there,
because on the other...
>> No, it's right there; it's
right there; it's right there.
>> We need to go.
>> PROBST: Timbira now slowing
down.
(indistinct talking)
>> That's it. That's it.
>> Let me get up a little quick.
(groans in pain)
All right, hold on.
Go.
>> Coming down.
>> PROBST: Jalapao slides
another piece into place.
If they're right, they are very
close to winning immunity.
Timbira losing their lead.
>> (shouts indistinctly)
>> PROBST: It's gonna be very
close.
Each tribe has one crate left.
>> You got it?
>> Yeah.
>> (yells)
>> PROBST: Sandy is getting
crushed by the crate.
>> Everyone grab a corner.
Jerry, help us out.
>> Help him pull it.
>> Jerry, pull it up.
>> Okay. Okay. I got it.
>> Now we have to turn it.
>> We got it.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Don't fall.
>> Hey, everything down here
fits.
>> PROBST: Jalapao has it!
Everybody's got to go up the
staircase!
>> Let's go! We got it!
We got it!
(shouts indistinctly)
>> PROBST: J.T.'s across!
Spencer's across!
Jalapao wins immunity!
(cheering, shouting, whooping)
♪ ♪
>> I'm beat.
>> PROBST: Jalapao,
congratulations.
>> (whoops)
>> Yeah!
>> There you go, girl.
>> (laughs)
>> PROBST: Jalapao, I got
nothing for you.
You guys have the night off.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> (whoops)
>> PROBST: Timbira, momentum has
definitely shifted.
Three straight wins by Jalapao.
Another loss, another trip to
Tribal Council, another tribe
member going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal
tonight.
>> I feel a great deal of
responsibility for the loss
today because I couldn't give it
my all.
I'm weak. I'm-I'm real weak.
My stomach just feels so bad.
It's like, uh, somebody's in
there with... two boxers in
there boxing around.
But, uh, I'm pretty sure that
everybody started looking at me
like, uh, "Jerry's not getting
any better.
He's probably the weakest link
on the tribe, so maybe get rid
of him."
(bird squawks)
>> How you feeling, Jerry?
Better?
>> I'm gonna go take a dip.
>> Okay.
>> Jerry, there's some extra
water over here.
Do you want me to fill your
canteen?
You sure?
>> Yeah, I got plenty here.
But I felt pretty good when we
went down and got that first
block, but after that all my
energy was zapped.
But I'm trying to... trying
to... endure.
Trying to tough it out best I
can.
I'm not gonna quit, though.
That's for sure.
I'm not a quitter.
(chuckles)
They got to vote me out.
I'm not giving up.
>> I think we had a
communication breakdown at some
point today, and I can't quite
figure out what it was.
>> We got this, we're just...
it's just the beginning of the
game.
>> We're just one behind.
We're one person behind now.
>> Yeah, it's, like, no big
deal; we'll figure it out.
Is Jerry okay?
>> The beans are making him
sick, and that's all we... you
know, we can't eat all the rice.
>> Shut up.
>> 'Cause he won't eat the
beans.
>> He can't... he hasn't eaten,
really, in... since you've left.
>> The most unfortunate thing
about this whole situation is
that as soon as Erinn realized
that Jerry was not sick, she
turned around and looked at the
tribe with the evil sneer, kind
of like...
"I'm staying."
>> What?
>> I'm so pissed off, man.
When she saw Jerry, it
registered that she was still
staying.
She went... I'm not kidding
you; I practiced her look.
She went like this.
It was the evilest look.
I can't stand it, man.
>> That's why I'm talking to
Jerry and telling him to stay
strong so we can get rid of her.
>> I think my relationship with
Tyson started out like head
coach/assistant coach.
But I go to him first because
if he's my right-hand man, if
he's my general, then I want to
make sure that we're clear with
our orders.
>> Let's still go with Erinn.
But Debbie and Sierra, those are
the two I'm gonna have to talk
to.
>> I mean, we're only as strong
as our weakest link.
>> Well, yeah, she did know she
was going home if Jerry wasn't
sick.
>> Yeah, and it just makes me
sick because I-I exist... to
surround myself with people that
have integrity, and I cannot
exist around people like that.
You guys can because you can
socialize with them.
I am so true... that existing
around people that smile evilly
when somebody else is on their
knees kills me.
I can't exist around... I can't
look at her in camp, I can't
walk by her now.
>> Coach is definitely pissed
about voting out Jerry, but I am
honestly not going to sever off
another limb so that we can get
our vendettas against Erinn.
>> She's still an asset to a
certain extent.
In the beginning when they saw
me sick and they saw me weak,
they were gonna vote me out.
So, as much as I have grown to
actually like and be fond of
Jerry, I'm not gonna be stupid.
>> You gotta stay strong, man.
You gotta...
stick it in there if you can,
you know.
Don't... yeah, don't give up.
>> Yeah.
What do you have in mind?
>> Erinn.
>> Erinn?
>> She was right on board with
Candace.
To me, it looks like she's just
here to lie and deceive and...
you know, get ahead any way
she can.
>> Has anybody been talking
about voting me out?
>> No, nobody has.
You try and look as strong as
you can.
Don't say anything to anybody.
>> Yeah.
(thunder rumbling)
>> With Tribal Council coming, I
I knew I only had a couple of
hours to get my act together
and go look for the idol, and so
I immediately kind of went to
the one place that made the
most sense to me, and that was
kind of the statue next to tree
mail.
And I got up to it, and, like,
started shaking the thing, and
nothing happened.
And I finally just, like, pushed
it out and, like, tried to look
underneath it because I thought
it might be there.
It wasn't there.
And then just started kind of
feeling around and looking at
the skirt, and then kind of
lifted up the skirt on the
backside of it and saw a little
hole and there was the idol.
Yes!
That makes not eating for a
couple of days worth it.
Good, good, good news.
It all worked out.
You know, the plan worked,
which was perfect.
As an entrepreneur, when I
think about business, like, to
me it was never about making
money, and even with Survivor
it's not about making money.
I love winning games, I love
playing games, competing and
winning them.
So as long as you're focused on
doing something that you love
and you're playing the game the
right way, good stuff happens.
Keep my fingers crossed.
>> Jerry, you want some beans?
>> Like you don't want to be
like, hey, everybody, Jerry's
sick, but you kind of want to be
sick.
And trying to, like, wrestle
with all these options of,
like, how do you bring it up
delicately, how do you make it
look like you're not trying to
throw someone under the bus or
save your own ass because every
time we send someone home who
doesn't want to be here it
leaves a space for someone who
does and I want to be here so
see you, Jerry.
>> Where's the thumb meter?
Sideways?
>> I'm doing better.
Thumb is sideways right now.
It was down; now it's sideways.
>> It's moving up.
>> Yeah, it's moving up.
Taste of a good cheeseburger,
I'd be back on top.
(laughing)
>> Yeah, I think Jerry's
illness has put a couple of
eyeballs on him.
I mean, if he's in pain and
can't compete in the
challenges, if he's the weak
link and it comes to Tribal
Council, he could be the next
one to go.
But anytime there's a
blindside, it's pretty awesome,
just the look on somebody's
face.
I think Erinn wants to be here
so, so bad, that her getting
blindsided would look really
cool.
I love seeing people cry when
you crush their dreams.
>> PROBST: Tyson, let's
talk about momentum.
Jalapao clearly has it.
How important is it in a game
like this?
>> Momentum's extremely
important.
I think we got a little bit
arrogant, and they're on a high
right now, and we're on a low.
I mean, it doesn't take much to
regain momentum, just a win.
If we can all focus and get
together then it can flip-flop
pretty fast.
>> PROBST: Well, what I noticed
today in the challenge was Erinn
right off the bat said, "I have
a plan, let's follow it," and it
was over.
>> That's exactly what
happened.
I said, "This piece goes here."
Everybody said, "No, no, no,
that's not right."
People panicked and we all did
nothing and then went, "Oh,
yeah, okay, that is right."
And it was too late by then.
>> PROBST: How frustrating is
that for you when you felt like
you knew it all along?
>> I...
it was just frustrating.
>> PROBST: Brendan, do you think
this group communicates as well
as it needs to?
>> I think we communicate very
well.
>> PROBST: Jerry, you were
shaking your head back and
forth as fast as you could.
>> Well, for instance, in
today's challenge, if we'd of
had a controlling person to say,
"Okay, you got it; we're all
going to listen to you, bam."
But that didn't happen.
We just need to establish a
leader.
>> PROBST: Who should it be,
Jerry?
>> I think it should be...
Brendan.
>> PROBST: Coach, you agree with
that; Brendan's the guy that
should be leading this tribe?
>> Being the devil's advocate,
let's say Brendan is the
leader; he has to take the
reins.
I'm not suggesting that I'm the
leader, but on the truck I was
making eye contact with
everybody and the reason why it
worked so smoothly is because I
basically told everybody with
my eyes to get what they needed
to get.
>> PROBST: So it sounds like you
should be leading.
>> Well, absolutely, I would
love to be leader.
That's what I'm used to doing.
>> PROBST: Erinn you had about
five different reactions.
Just share one with me.
>> I think it's a role that
Coach is used to.
It's a role that he would love
to be in, but it's something
that Brendan does better.
>> PROBST: Coach?
>> Again, I'm not criticizing
Brendan, but we've lost three
challenges in a row and for her
to be so quick to say that, I
think comes more to a
personality clash between us
two.
>> I didn't know we had a
personality clash.
You have these great ideas, but
I don't ever see you saying
more than, "Well, I have this
idea, but you guys do whatever
you're going to do."
>> PROBST: So you're saying
he's a little
passive-aggressive, throwing
throwing out an idea, but not
owning it?
>> Uh-huh.
>> PROBST: Coach, is that hard
to hear?
'Cause it sounds like what
you're struggling with a little
bit is ego.
>> It's not about ego because
I would rather toe the line and
be a good assistant coach than
try to be a head coach and
stroke my ego.
What I was doing was I
was justifying why I should be
the leader, and why I registered
surprise when Erinn said it's
Brendan.
>> PROBST: Jerry, how is
tonight's vote going to make
this tribe better?
>> I think tonight's vote will
make this tribe better because
it will get rid of the weakest
person.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Coach, you're up.
>> I hope you feel better.
>> Love you, sweetheart, but we
made a decision.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Jerry.
Jerry.
Two votes Jerry.
Erinn.
Two votes Jerry; one vote Erinn.
Jerry.
That's three votes Jerry;
one vote Erinn.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins: Jerry.
That's four; that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Jerry, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, according to you guys,
tonight's vote was all about
making this tribe stronger.
Time will tell if you made the
right decision or not.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT NETWORK
TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: at Jalapao,
Sydney turns on the charm.
>> I definitely try to flirt
when it comes to this game.
>> PROBST: And the Timbira tribe
loses their heads...
while Taj keeps hers in the
game.
>> As far as my experiences in
Afghanistan and the military
career, this by far was the
toughest thing I have endured
in my life.
I don't know what happened to
my stomach, but in 130-degree
heat and me not being able to
eat anything took a toll on my
body.
I'm hoping and praying that one
of my tribe members will win
that million dollars.