>> JEFF PROBST: This is Brazil,
known for its beautiful people,
the world's greatest soccer,
spectacular beaches, and the
most vibrant and dynamic cities
in the world.
But for these 16 Americans,
their adventure will play out in
one of the most deserted and
unforgiving sections of Brazil:
Tocantins.
The temperatures in this high
desert are brutal and can top
120 degrees.
(thunder rumbling)
And sudden storms can ignite
dangerous wildfires in an
instant.
This vast region covers over
100,000 square miles and is one
of the most isolated places on
earth.
The rivers, if you can find
them, provide the only source of
water, but you'll have to share
it with every other wild animal
trying to survive.
(roaring)
(hooting)
They've traveled for days to
get here.
They've already been divided
into two tribes: Jalapao in
red, and Timbira in black.
And although no one has spoken
to each other, first impressions
are already forming.
>> Tall, spiky hair, model boy.
Love him.
He just seems like a good guy to
have around.
>> The younger brunette-- she
comes off to me as kind of being
the bitch.
>> We have the strung-out old
lady, and it is sort of
encouraging to have her because
you know you're not going to be
the first to go.
>> The real tall boy-- I think
he's like a geek.
I think I should be able to lead
him around real easy.
>> I've been sick.
I got some bad tonsils.
I've been trying to hide it so
I don't get voted off.
>> This blond-- I have an
unfortunate feeling she's going
to crumble.
>> PROBST: They come from
different walks of life--
16 Americans forced to work
together to create a new society
while battling the elements and
each other.
They must learn to adapt
or they'll be voted out.
In the end, only one will remain
to claim the million-dollar
prize.
39 days, 16 people,
one survivor.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Welcome to Survivor:
Tocantins.
You guys ready to get this game
started?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yes!
>> Let's go.
>> PROBST: We have our two
tribes: Jalapao in red,
Timbira in black.
Now you're going to get your
first chance to work together.
This truck is loaded with
supplies that will make your
stay here in Brazil a bit
easier.
You will have 60 seconds to
gather as much as you can.
Your time starts now 'cause
this game is on.
>> Come on.
>> Get down.
I'll hand this to you.
>> Right here! Right here!
>> Hey, get down, dude.
>> Do it right here, right here.
>> Here you go, come on.
>> Yeah, we got 'em now.
>> I got 'em. I got 'em.
>> Incoming.
(woman yells)
(overlapping chatter)
>> Hey, hey, hey, hey.
>> All right, here we go.
>> PROBST: Everything you can
get your hands on.
>> Go, go...
>> PROBST: If for no other
reason than to make sure the
other tribe doesn't get it.
>> Ooh.
>> PROBST: Don't break it.
It's no good broken.
>> Do it.
(grunting)
>> Yeah, right here.
>> Come on, come on.
Water's the most important.
>> PROBST: Ten seconds left.
>> Flag's right here.
Flag's right here.
> Hand me the water!
Hand me the water!
>> PROBST: Five, four.
>> Let go.
>> PROBST: Three, two...
one.
That's it!
Everybody off.
All right, first impressions.
Guy in the black shirt.
What did you notice about your
tribe?
>> It seemed like we all knew
what we were going to get.
We got all the water.
We got all beans.
We got everything we needed.
>> PROBST: Did you realize that?
You guys have no water, and you
didn't get any of the bags of
food.
>> Yeah, we, uh...
We'll be all right.
We'll make do.
>> PROBST: Take a look around.
Brazilian Highlands.
Beautiful part of Brazil, but
extremely harsh.
It's 110 right now, and it's
early.
You are going to be hot.
You're going to get wet.
Here's a map and a compass to
your new home.
It's about a four-hour trek...
(gasps and scoffs)
...to your camp.
You've got a lot of stuff to
carry, and it's about to get
just a little bit more
difficult.
We're going to have our first
vote.
And one person from each tribe
is not going to make this
journey.
>> Game on.
Let's play it hard right from
the beginning.
Let's get rid of the weak
players even before we start,
and this is going to set the
tone for the whole time.
>> PROBST: Very little
information to base this vote
on.
First impressions go a long way
in this game.
All right, one at a time.
We're going to reveal votes.
We're going to start with
Jalapao.
>> I wrote down Grammy.
>> PROBST: Who's Grammy?
>> Grammy's going to be the
old... the older lady.
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Sandy.
>> PROBST: Sandy.
>> Two for Sandy.
>> PROBST: Okay, that's two for
Sandy.
>> Guy with glasses in peachy
orange shirt.
>> Stephen.
>> PROBST: Stephen.
That's two for Sandy;
one vote for Stephen.
>> Three for Sandy.
>> PROBST: That is three for
Sandy.
>> The older lady. For Sandy.
I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: That is four for
Sandy, one for Stephen.
>> Older lady, Sandy.
I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: That's five.
There's only eight.
Five is enough.
Sandy, over here with me.
Sandy, you can't be happy about
this.
>> I'm pissed.
I am so pissed.
Obviously, I didn't know it was
going to be like this, as far
as them being able to vote
before, you know, we got to know
each other or whatever.
But I bet one of the youngest
ones drops out first.
We'll see who can handle the
heat.
>> PROBST: All right, Timbira.
Let's see what damage you've
done.
>> I said gray and black
striped T-shirt.
She just looked really hot on
the trip.
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Sierra.
>> PROBST: Sierra.
That's one for Sierra.
>> Zebra-striped top.
>> PROBST: Two for Sierra.
You look shocked already,
Sierra.
>> Yeah, well, I have strep
throat.
So, I got it three days ago, and
I'm on antibiotics right now,
so...
>> Sierra. Sorry.
>> PROBST: Sierra.
That is three for Sierra.
>> Purple tank with the ruffles?
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Erinn.
>> PROBST: That's three votes
Sierra; one vote Erinn.
>> Blond girl with jeans and
striped shirt.
>> PROBST: That is four for
Sierra.
One more, and you're out,
>> Young lady, blonde, with the
black and white blouse-- Sierra.
>> PROBST: Sierra, that's five.
That's enough.
Head over.
Sierra, you look angry and
shocked.
>> I think I could have brought
a lot to this team.
Um, I'm sorry I have a fever of
102, but if that's your choice,
fine by me.
>> PROBST: Well, let's be clear.
I said you will not take part in
this adventure.
(gasping)
This adventure is a four-hour
trek to camp.
(laughter, Sandy screams)
You guys both made very strong
first impressions.
The good news is, you get a
chance to change those
impressions because while
these guys are trekking for four
hours, carrying all of the camp
supplies, you're going to fly to
camp in a helicopter.
>> Thank you, God!
>> PROBST: I wouldn't be
celebrating, Sandy.
This is a game about social
integration.
You have been outcast
immediately.
This wasn't even close.
Smiles is not what I'd be doing.
I'd be thinking about, how do I
start working to change an
impression that I have given
these guys?
You guys have a long journey
ahead of you.
You need to get to camp.
You need to start working on
shelter.
>> All right.
>> Let's take some.
(helicopter blades whirring)
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
have some work to do if you want
to stay in this game.
Bird's coming in.
Head on over.
Have a good flight.
(grunts)
>> Yoo-ha!
(bird screeching)
>> Has anybody ever wanted to
come to Brazil?
>> Yes!
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> This thing is getting heavy.
>> Hey, you guys, hold up.
Wait for us!
>> My partial motivation for
being here is to get rid of the
rest of the my baby weight.
>> I like it.
>> I got you. I got you.
>> I'm gonna melt it off in this
damn heat.
>> Work that off, girl!
>> I am 19 years old.
As far as I know, I'm the
youngest contestant ever on
Survivor.
And I am obsessed with it.
I have watched every season.
And I love the physical aspect.
I like the challenges.
But the trek was treacherous.
It-It was hot.
The sun was high.
It was not easy, by any means.
>> Are we going the right way,
Joe?
>> Is this way okay?
>> Uh, hold up, J.T. Hold on.
Let's just make sure we're going
the right way.
Are you all cool with that?
>> Okay.
>> You know how to read that,
right?
>> Remember the compass always
faced north.
>> Compass 101.
>> You want to put the
compass...
>> Yeah, so it faces north.
>> ...down with the map so it
faces north.
>> Well, we can't do that,
'cause it's always going to
face that way.
>> Okay.
>> Uh-oh.
>> Turn that map like that.
>> We're trading places.
>> There you go.
>> Yes.
>> I'm J.T., I'm 24 years old,
and I'm from Samson, Alabama.
I manage a Black Angus cattle
ranch.
I'm in hot weather every day,
so I'm accustomed to the
weather and mosquitoes, things
of that nature.
>> All you do is find 112 and
line it up.
>> I mean, it's right...
literally right at the notch.
>> I know I'm going to be good
at catching fish.
And I know I'm going to be good
at providing, but that'll also
put me out in front of everybody
else as a threat eventually.
The biggest challenge for me is
going to be fitting in with the
people.
>> What happened to your leg?
>> No, just from the water...
>> Yeah, you have a hole in your
pants.
>> Oh, yeah, my ass is ripped.
>> Got some booty hanging out on
the first day.
>> You know, this is going to be
nice for the ladies back home.
When I saw at least one, sort of
good, old-fashioned Southern
boy, I thought I'm a little bit
screwed.
Don't really see us connecting
on too many levels.
I don't know how much he's going
to like the anxious New York
Jew.
>> The farther we walk north is
going to be farther.
So, if we're veering to the
left, we're cutting the whole
corner off.
>> It's a good point.
>> Yeah. Fair enough?
>> I'm not trying to be bossy or
anything.
>> No, I like it.
If it gets us there sooner,
do it.
>> If it gets us to Sandy
sooner, I am all for that.
>> To Sandy.
>> Sandy.
>> Psycho Sandy.
>> Perfect.
>> Yeah, follow J.T.
>> Just kind of keep me lined
up, Joe.
>> Yeah.
♪ ♪
>> Come on, guys.
We can do it.
>> This is hard.
>> Yeah.
What the hell am I doing out
here?
I'm a hairstylist.
The last time I went camping, I
was maybe in the seventh grade.
(screams)
>> Sorry, sorry.
>> Are you okay?
>> (laughing): Yeah.
>> Break time?
>> We had a mishap.
>> Dude, what else do you do to
stay in shape?
>> Eat potato chips, watch TV.
(laughing)
>> No, seriously.
You gotta do something else.
>> I work out.
I go to the gym.
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah, I go to a gym.
I just got back from Afghanistan
on a 12-month tour.
I'm with the South Carolina
Army National Guard.
And I am a first sergeant.
I have 100 men under me.
I stay pretty active.
And I know how to give orders.
But in Survivor, everybody has
their own individual mind, so
I'm going to try to keep it
low-key as I can because I
don't want to be in charge.
If you're in charge, you don't
last too long.
>> Here's where we started.
>> Head 91 degrees east.
>> And we have to go all the way
until we find...
>> All the way until we find a
palm tree.
>> I consider myself a
Renaissance man/adventurer.
I'm a university head soccer
coach, and the polar opposite of
that is that I'm the conductor
and artistic director of a
symphony in Northern California.
We're going to go there, stop,
look at the compass, look at the
map again.
I'm always used to being a
leader, by inspiring, pulling
out the best in everybody
because as we all know, a team
is only as good as its weakest
player.
I want to tell you something.
I want to change this game.
It's survival of the weakest.
It's survival of the people that
can't survive in the wild, and
you and I can change this game
by making the strong survive.
If we look back at our
ancestors, whether it be
American Indian, whether it be
the Norse Vikings, whether it be
the samurai warrior, they prayed
for an opponent that was worthy
enough to defeat them, and died
with honor and glory in
the battle.
So, I know I'm making myself
honorable to you by letting it
that out of the bag first.
But that's what I'm talking
about... you and me change the
game.
>> Coach, like right away, he
came in and said, "I want to
tell you how I'm playing this
game."
But it kind of throws up a red
flag being, one, is he lying,
and two, we're here to play and
to win a game, and I don't think
any of us wants a coach in that
process.
>> Iron sharpens iron, baby.
Say, let's rock 'n' roll, okay.
>> All right, let's go.
>> Let's rock 'n' roll.
♪ ♪
>> My tribe had to, like, travel
by foot and, you know, I got to
ride in the helicopter,
but I couldn't take it all in
because I was still pissed,
because the first thing they
want to do is get rid of the-the
old gal.
Oh, wow.
I'm glad I'm here first.
And then they can't see me, uh,
with the emotion of the first
vote.
It scared me so bad.
But now I'm-I'm gonna...
I'm gonna make it to 39 days.
I'm going to show 'em.
Because maybe I am the older
woman, but I'm older and I'm
wiser.
And this game is mine.
That's what I believe with all
my heart.
So let the games begin.
♪ ♪
(gasps)
>> Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
"Welcome to camp.
Your tribe chose to leave you
behind.
Now it's your turn to make a
decision.
You have a few hours before
your tribe arrives.
You can start setting up your
camp, which may curry favor
with your new tribe mates, or
you can use this time to search
for a hidden immunity idol,
which would guarantee your
safety the first time
Jalapeño..." I don't know how
to say that, whatever, okay...
"goes to Tribal Council.
So what do you do?"
I'm looking for the idol.
That's what I'm doing.
"You better hurry.
Your tribe is on its way.
Clue one: a stick marks the
spot on your biggest beach.
Dig for a while and assistance
you'll reach."
Oh, my God.
Okay.
I'm going to the beach, and I'm
going to go find my idol.
Oh, my God!
When I first got here and I
seen, you know, the supplies or
whatever, some wood laying there
and-and stuff and rope, I
thought I can go back there and
try to make up this camp, you
know, that they probably won't
even like anyway because it's...
a woman made it.
And it still ain't going to keep
my name off that piece of paper.
So I'm going to look for the
idol.
And that's the bottom line,
'cause you gotta look out for
#1, and that's me.
♪ ♪
>> I'm here at Timbira alone
because I was looked at as a
weakness, which was very
hurtful.
But, um, they don't know me at
all.
I bring a lot, a lot of good
strengths to this.
Oh.
And there's a note.
It says, "Welcome to camp.
Your tribe chose to leave you
behind."
Thanks a lot.
"You can start setting up camp
or you can use this time to
search for a hidden immunity
idol, which would guarantee
your safety the first time
Timbira goes to Tribal Council.
So what do you do?"
People may think this is a
really stupid idea, but, um...
I'm going to continue to build
my camp.
They say that first impressions
are everlasting but, hopefully,
I'll change their opinion of me.
Yeah, I could go and try to look
for an immunity idol and protect
my butt, but my prerogative is
looking good in the eyes of my
crew.
I mean, if you don't redeem
yourself, I'm pretty much in the
doghouse forever.
>> Have you seen a tarantula
yet, J.T.?
>> Not yet.
You will know when I see a
tarantula.
>> I guess we're going the right
way.
Keep going.
>> Tell me you see the flag.
>> I see it.
>> Whoo!
Finally!
>> Jalapao!
>> Before sundown.
>> There is a god!
(distant chattering)
>> Oh, no, my tribe's here.
I gotta hide this note.
>> Whoo!
>> Sandy!
>> They look even?
>> Sandy?
Is that you?
(laughter)
>> Hi, Sandy!
>> Hi.
>> Whoo!
Hi!
I'm so sorry.
>> Look.
Look at this. Look at this.
>> We had just trekked four
hours carrying pots and
watermelons, and then we get
here and it's, like, Sandy
didn't do anything.
And I was just like, great.
You've been chilling here, and I
still gotta do stuff.
>> I don't care what you call me
as long as you keep me on your
tribe.
Everybody was kind of just all
laughs and smiles, and they had
just all written my name down.
But, you know, screw you.
Because, you know, the bottom
line is this... when we go to
Tribal Council, you're going to
write down my name again.
Now, why the hell do I even want
to waste my energy on trying to
get in your good graces when I
wasn't even ever there...
it wasn't an option.
You all are here.
Okay, yes, and look...
>> How do you say our name?
>> I know said "Jalapeño."
>> Jalapeño.
>> I know when what I have to
do, and that's find that idol.
I'd like to outwit them or, you
know, trick 'em one time, at
least let 'em write down my name
and say, "No, looky, I got the
idol."
You know, I would love to do
that.
♪ ♪
>> Go slow.
>> Yup.
>> 'Cause I can't see.
>> Watch out for those holes.
Try and step over 'em, I guess.
>> We've got to get fired up
here.
It may be midnight, but we're
going to make it.
>> Oh, dude, our flags.
>> There's our flag, baby, yay!
>> Yes!
Thank gosh.
>> Uh-oh, Sierra.
>> Whoo!
>> Good job.
>> I see lots and lots of
lumber.
>> Sierra?
>> We're home.
>> Where are you?
>> Thank you.
>> So you guys, all I want to
say is I was kind of really sick
and I was hiding it because I
thought it was a weakness.
Yeah, I probably would've voted
for myself not knowing what was
wrong with me because I did
look like I was tired.
>> But you couldn't have done
what we did today.
>> I couldn't because I have a
fever.
>> Sierra, she's a great, sweet
kid.
She's got a sweet spirit.
She did do a lot of work and,
of course, we appreciate that.
>> Did it change anything when
you found out that I was sick?
Did it make sense?
>> Yeah, yeah, no, it did.
Yeah, it made a big difference.
>> But, you know, let's face it:
you can't change what we did
together as a tribe.
It bonded all of us, and,
unfortunately, you know, Sierra
was not there, and obviously,
I'm pushing for the strong to
survive.
So, I think Sierra, even though
she's awesome, she's got to go.
♪ ♪
(birds squawking)
>> Yeah, we can all build a fire
together.
>> Lay these posts on the ground
and then lay these crossways,
and you're still that far off
the ground.
>> There you go.
>> Things at camp are shaping up
okay.
We've got our shelter built now.
We haven't got our floor done,
but it's gonna get better.
We're going to work on it
a little more.
>> You need to get this one back
up there, and the good thing
about it is, we'll have extra
left so we can, like, either
make a chair or put, like, a
wall up.
>> Do you think that's going to
be worth it?
>> I don't know. I'm...
>> It's going to take us all
day.
>> That's a lot of work.
I don't know if I want to start
that right now.
>> Let's try to get everything
done as soon as possible and
then relax.
It's hard for me to keep my
opinions to myself, but I'm
hoping that my tribe really
understands that shelter is
extremely important and that we
buckle down and get that going.
>> So what I'm going to do-- I'm
going to go use the restroom,
and then I'm going to take up
anything I think we might need.
I don't know.
Is that cool?
>> Yeah.
>> That's totally cool.
>> All right, so I'm going to
mosey on down this 'a way.
>> All right.
>> Okay, I bought myself a few
minutes, and I'm going over here
to the beach to see if I can't
find that idol again.
Okay, I'm looking for the idol
here because this was the stick
that marks the spot.
I hope and pray.
(panting)
Oh.
(whimpers)
Oh, my God.
Oh, God!
Ooh!
Okay.
"Ten paces you'll walk towards
the lone palm tree.
Dig in the sand, the next clue
you will see."
Ten paces?
Ten. I wonder what a pace is.
All right, pace gods, give me a
clue of how many paces.
I don't know.
What's a pace?
>> She went looking for stuff.
>> Oh, okay.
>> By herself?
>> Yeah.
>> One, two, three, four...
Eight, nine, ten.
And finally.
This is so brutal.
I can't imagine, #1,
what ten paces is.
And there was a lone palm tree
for my next clue.
I'm really at a loss right now,
but I'm definitely not gonna
give up looking for that idol.
Oh, for God's sake.
>> That's it.
No more water.
Water is out.
>> We've already emptied the
water that we pulled off the
truck, so me, Debbie, and Tyson
decided to go down and fill up
our canteen.
(laughing)
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh!
>> Being from Utah, you'd think
I'd be a shirt and tie, nerdy
glasses, but I'm probably not
the stereotypical Mormon.
>> He's naked!
>> Wow.
>> I'm probably more of a free
spirit.
>> Well, he doesn't want his
clothes wet for the challenge.
(Sierra screaming)
(Sierra laughs)
>> Having somebody that can make
you laugh in an environment like
this where everybody is dirty
and tired-- I think people
appreciate that.
>> Oh, my God.
>> You can look if you want...
>> It's your show, Tyson.
>> But when it comes down to it,
I want that million dollars--
exotic expensive furs on my
shoulder, jewels on these pretty
fingers.
We're talking big time.
I'll wear a tiara, a man tiara.
Do they make those?
>> Tyson!
Don't even know.
>> Look at 'em. Look at 'em.
(screams and laughs)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Guys ready to get to your first
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, six members of each
tribe will race across a series
of sand hills and into the
river.
You must then retrieve your raft
loaded with puzzle planks.
Once you have the raft back to
shore, you'll untie the ropes,
release puzzle planks.
You'll then race those puzzle
planks back to the start where
the two remaining tribe members
will use those puzzle planks to
build a staircase.
Each puzzle plank is different
and must be placed at the
corresponding step.
Once you have all your tribe
members to the top of the
staircase, any two tribe members
must work together to navigate a
peg through a table maze,
allowing you to release your
tribe's flag.
First tribe to raise their flag
wins.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Please.
>> PROBST: First of all, you are
playing for fire.
>> Ooh!
(whooping)
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: Fire in the form of
flint.
In addition, you are playing for
the most important thing in this
game.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: Immunity.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Immunity guarantees
you cannot be voted out.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Give you a minute to
strategize, and we will get
started.
Building a staircase for
Jalapao: Taj and Sandy.
Building the staircase for
Timbira: Sierra and Erinn.
Everybody else is running.
Here we go.
For fire and immunity...
survivors ready?
Go!
(overlapping chatter)
You can run, jump, fly over
these hills.
Attack them.
(grunting and panting)
>> Move it!
>> Fast, ladies. Come on!
>> (shouting) Look!
>> PROBST: J.T. ahead of the
pack.
>> Go...
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: Everybody's got to
get to the raft before you can
unclip.
>> Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Go. Go.
>> That's it.
>> PROBST: Both tribes at the
raft at the same time.
Jalapao heading back with their
raft.
Timbira heading back with their
>> Get away! Get away!
>> PROBST: Carolina struggling
to stay up.
>> Come on, Caroline.
You can do it!
>> PROBST: Tyson really pulling
the weight for Timbira.
>> Tyson!
>> PROBST: You cannot start
working on this till everybody's
across the line.
Everybody.
Let's go!
Red, you're good.
Black, you're good.
Start untying those planks and
get them back to the start.
>> Just slide them out.
>> Let's go.
>> PROBST: Joe heading back for
Jalapao.
>> Come on, Joe!
>> PROBST: Tyson taking a big
heavy load for Timbira.
>> Good job, Tyson!
>> Come on, Joe!
>> Joe.
>> Come on, Joe.
>> On the mat or on the wood?
>> Just put it right here.
>> PROBST: Carolina and Sydney
struggling.
>> Are there any planks left?
>> BOTH: No.
>> This is all?
>> PROBST: Once all the planks
are back, you can start working
on that staircase.
>> Good job, guys.
No slowing down.
>> PROBST: Timbira has all of
theirs.
It's 120 degrees today.
Already taking its toll.
Three days in Brazil, and
people are struggling.
>> Under that or on that?
It seems it's got to be on the
other end.
>> Set that one over there.
>> PROBST: Timbira, start
working on your staircase.
>> Okay, go.
>> PROBST: Jalapao, you've got
to get your last planks back.
>> Come on, kids, there you go.
Y'all bring me some planks,
baby.
>> PROBST: Jalapao, start
working on it.
Everybody's working on their
staircase.
(overlapping chatter)
>> Okay. Okay.
One, one.
>> PROBST: Sandy and Taj working
it for Jalapao.
Erinn and Sierra working it for
Timbira.
>> Okay, I need three wide on
the left.
>> PROBST: Jalapao starting to
pull ahead a little bit.
>> On the right.
>> The next, get three and
three.
>> PROBST: Erinn and Sierra not
panicking, though.
Keeping their calm, taking
their time.
Sierra getting involved now for
Timbira.
>> This one's next!
>> PROBST: Sandy calling the
shots for Jalapao.
The two people nobody wanted are
now leading their tribes.
>> It's the three-three,
no spaces.
That's it.
>> PROBST: Jalapao increasing
their lead now.
>> Okay, try this one!
Erinn.
>> Give me another board!
>> PROBST: Jalapao with their
last piece.
>> That's it!
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: Sandy and Taj giving
Jalapao a huge lead.
>> Right here, right here, right
here, right here.
>> Oh, it's very lumpy.
It's going to float.
>> PROBST: Jalapao working on
the final table maze.
>> Pull yours down.
Let's see. Pull yours down.
>> PROBST: Sierra fighting hard
to keep her tribe in it.
>> We got it.
Give me another one!
>> PROBST: You're very close,
Timbira, very close.
Hold it, guys.
>> Yeah, there you go.
There you go.
>> Don't let 'em!
>> PROBST: Timbira, two steps
away from being back in it.
>> You guys got it.
>> PROBST: Timbira completes
their staircase.
Two people inside.
A tough first challenge with
immunity on the line.
Timbira working well together.
Erinn and Brendan moving
quickly through this maze.
>> Back. Your back.
>> No, this way's wrong.
>> PROBST: Both Spencer and
Sydney struggling a little bit.
>> Keep it high.
Keep it high like that.
>> PROBST: Timbira has erased
the lead Jalapao had.
We're very even right now.
>> Find now.
Find the rail first.
>> It's the middle road.
The middle road on this next
turn.
>> PROBST: Immunity on the line.
Nobody wants to go to Tribal
Council.
Nothing good ever happens at
Tribal Council.
>> It's hot. It's hot.
>> PROBST: Timbira now with a
bit of a lead, if they are
right.
>> Hold it out.
>> Take your time.
>> PROBST: Timbira very close.
>> PROBST: Brendan and Erinn
can smell it.
>> Take your time.
>> PROBST: First challenge, the
first win is this close.
>> Bring 'em up!
>> Four, three, two, one.
>> PROBST: That's it!
(screaming and cheering)
Timbira wins immunity!
>> Yeah!
(screams and indistinct chatter)
>> One, two, three!
>> Timbira!
>> PROBST: Timbira,
congratulations.
Fire.
>> Yeah!
>> Fire.
>> PROBST: That will make camp
life a lot easier, right?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: And immunity.
>> Yeah, right!
>> PROBST: No Tribal Council for
Timbira.
Nobody going home.
Jalapao, bad news for you guys.
Tribal Council tonight.
The first person will be voted
out of this game, and it's
coming from your tribe.
You will have the afternoon to
figure out who it's gonna be.
Head back to camp.
>> That's sweet!
>> We got... (indistinct)
>> Tribal Council was the one
thing that I was dreading
because I don't want to vote
for Sandy.
I mean, she worked her ass off
at the challenge.
But I don't know who else to
vote for.
>> Anybody want to go to the
water real quick?
>> Yeah.
>> The water.
>> The challenge-- it was just
heartbreaking.
The vote's for Sandy,
unfortunately.
But with every failure, there's
an opportunity for growth.
That's one of my #1 sayings.
What can our tribe do better at
camp?
Maybe we could be a little bit
more organized.
>> Like our shelter.
You know, it...
>> You know, it's the stuff like
that, we'd love to just do it
all at once, but we're
dehydrated and hungry and human.
>> Oh, I totally agree.
I totally agree.
But it's just, like, you know,
like, and the...
You know, when it gets a little
cooler today, let-let's wrap it
up, so, like...
>> But how would that help us in
challenges?
>> I'm just making a suggestion.
>> Oh, I know.
Don't... Don't get defensive.
Just listen for a second.
>> Yeah. We're all gonna say
something.
>> So, you know, when we first
came back, we're hot, we're
exhausted, we're lost, and the
first thing you're going to tell
somebody is you need to clean
up.
Clean up the outdoors?!
Are you kidding me?
Basically, I just...
And I mean, you can listen.
I don't care.
But I just wanted to tell you.
Sometimes you panic a bit, and
you get whiny.
>> Oh, I know.
>> You need to curb that
because it's only going to cause
tension in the group.
>> Yeah.
>> It's just going to cause
frustration.
>> I totally agree.
I'm just telling you my
viewpoint, and I totally agree.
>> No. I know, I know, and
that's why I'm pulling you aside
so you can understand.
I'm not going to tell anybody
else; I'm going to tell you.
>> Yeah. No, I agree.
>> So you can completely
understand what I'm talking
about.
>> Taj called me out, and she
was right.
When it comes to, like, working
or getting things done, you
know, I can get very opinionated
and do speak my mind.
>> All right...
>> Now, like, I've just been
thinking about checking myself.
(hooting)
>> I know, dude, right.
>> I mean, unless everybody else
is just dead set on getting rid
of Sandy-- which I would
disagree with-- I'm
wholeheartedly campaign Sandy or
whatever we want.
My first impression of Sandy was
that she might be a liability in
challenges, but she proved
today that, you know, not so
much.
She did a great job.
She's really into this, and it's
kind of like, why should we
just-just based on first
impressions, sort of, and for
no other reason, just kind of
get rid of her?
>> Just so you know what
happened and what this means for
Council or not, we get back to
the water, the first thing that,
uh, Caroline starts talking
about is how we need to finish
stuff around camp.
>> Um...
>> And honestly, I don't know if
Sandy outperformed her.
It was different tasks...
>> Yeah.
>> ...but I don't think...
I don't think Caroline stuck out
ahead of her.
Between Sandy and Caroline, it's
kind of a tricky decision, being
that it's pretty close as to how
they'll perform in future
challenges and how they'll add
to the morale of the camp.
The first option is obviously
Sandy, just based on how old
she is.
But, uh, Caroline can be very
bossy, and it's gotten worse.
So, in this environment, that
bossy streak will get old
really quick.
>> I just feel bad 'cause I
feel like you and I, like, when
I put down that "older lady"
from that vote.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> I felt like, you know, I know
that hurt your feelings, and
when I realized that it did,
like, I genuinely felt really
bad.
>> Right. You know.
>> And I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry for, like,
yesterday.
>> Yeah, yeah. Me too.
>> Yeah, yeah.
But that's okay.
You know, you don't have to be
sorry, you know, or anything,
but, um, you know, if I'm the
one to go, then that's just the
way it is.
I'm glad I'm here today, and
I'm hoping I'm going to be here
tomorrow.
But I believe my tribe is
voting for me.
So, um, I'm going to look for
that idol.
I'm definitely going to figure
out what ten paces are, and I'm
going to dig this time under
anything and everything, I
guess.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
approach the flame, dip it in
and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire, you're
still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
That will be the case for one
of you tonight.
All right, let's go back to the
beginning.
Sandy, within the first five
minutes, you were voted out of
your tribe based on the first
impression that you were simply
too old.
>> Well, I guess I summed it up
with the first response when I
said, "I'm pissed," because,
you know, I've got my heart in
this game, and I want to stay
in this game.
>> PROBST: J.T., what are you
guys talking about in regards to
Sandy?
You already voted her out.
Now, she gets a free ride back
to camp.
>> Well, we did that
strategically to try to make the
group stronger.
That was our point of view.
We hoped she'd be at least
rounding up wood or get a camp
picked out when we got there.
We didn't really know what to
expect.
>> PROBST: So, Sydney, you had
an expectation she better be at
camp doing something.
>> Definitely, and she
definitely greeted us with open
arms, but the next day, was a
little different than I thought
she was going to be.
She didn't really do much around
camp.
She was going off by herself a
lot.
>> PROBST: Sandy, let's explore
that for a minute.
It seems like after everything
you went through on day one, the
expectation would be, on day
two that you got some recovering
to do.
>> Sure, but I wanted to collect
my thoughts and get all that out
of my head so that I could go
back into them with nothing but
positive, which I did.
>> PROBST: And so, are you
trying to figure out, "Okay,
they're seeing me as an old
lady?"
>> Oh, I know.
>> PROBST: So do you start
thinking, "How do I change that
perception?"
>> No, because I'm the old lady,
no matter what.
But an old lady can also fit
into this tribe of all these
kids that could be mine.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Sandy, you a little
crazy?
>> Oh, I'm a lot crazy.
Yeah.
>> PROBST: So you're used to
people looking at you and kind
of going, "Hmm. Not sure.
Kind of amusing, a little odd."
>> Mm-hmm.
That's how it happens with me.
I don't know why, but I like it.
>> PROBST: Carolina, is it fair
to vote out Sandy just because
she's old?
She can't change that.
>> I don't necessarily think
that it's fair, but I felt like
our team voted smart.
And we could explain it 100
times, but it is what it is.
>> PROBST: What do you think the
first impression of you was?
>> I'm very boisterous, so I'm
not afraid to say my opinion.
And I could say that I came
across a little demanding to
get things done.
Sometimes, my directness comes
across like maybe a little
whiny, and I need to check
myself before I speak, and I
openly admit that.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to get to the vote.
J.T., you're up.
>> Carolina, I hope you're going
to be the first one voted out
and not me.
>> Sorry, Sandy.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Sandy.
Carolina.
That's two votes Carolina;
one vote Sandy.
Carolina.
Three votes Carolina;
one vote Sandy.
Carolina.
That's four votes Carolina;
one vote Sandy.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins: Carolina.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Carolina, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, two things are very clear
from tonight's Tribal Council:
you're willing to change your
first impressions, and you're
willing to blindside each other.
Good news about coming to
Tribal Council: you will go
home with fire.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> Oh, yes!
>> Yes!
>> Whoa.
>> Thank you!
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
The game is on.
>> Hold on to it, Sierra!
>> PROBST: J.T. not letting
Tyson get rid of that ball.
Candace trying to take Taj down.
>> Good job!
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: Candace has it for
Timbira.
And one shot changes everything.
>> I just got completely
blindsided.
I'm the first person voted off.
I'm not going to lie.
Like, I'm pissed off.
Like, this sucks.
It's embarrassing.
However, I'm going to be the
bigger person and wish them
well.
I think initially what got me
voted off was my mouth.
You know, it's a lesson learned,