>> PROBST: The first 15 days of
Survivor: Tocantins have seen
some of the most memorable
castaways yet.
They've been competing fiercely
in one of the most unforgiving
environments in the world.
This is what you've seen so
far.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Timbira wins immunity!
>> That's not okay.
>> Who the hell do you think
you are?
>> That will get old really
quick.
>> PROBST: Carolina, the tribe
has spoken.
Candace trying to take Taj down.
J.T. fakes out Jerry!
Jalapao wins.
You're now going to send one
member of Timbira to Exile
Island.
>> Now, to the twist, choose
one member of the winning tribe
to join you.
>> Taj.
>> You work Sierra.
I'll work Steve.
We would have a four-way
alliance that nobody knows
about.
>> That nobody knows about.
>> Exactly.
>> You're the best accomplice
ever.
>> I think they're going to be
under- or overcooked.
>> Hopefully, Candace has her
bags packed because she is out
of here.
>> PROBST: The tribe has spoken.
>> Debbie!
>> Brendan!
>> Debbie, where's our bucket?
>> I don't know.
I can't see it!
>> PROBST: Jalapao wins
immunity!
>> I found the idol.
Yes!
>> Hey, everybody, Jerry's sick.
See you, Jerry.
>> PROBST: Timbira does win
immunity!
>> I'm voting for Sandy because
she's crazy.
>> Do you want to be a part of
the biggest upset on Survivor
history?
>> Yes, I do.
>> Okay, stuff this in your
pocket.
Do something with it.
Hide it.
>> I might have just stumbled
ass-backwards into a huge
alliance.
>> J.T.!
>> PROBST: J.T., unbelievable!
>> Yeah, J.T.!
>> Launch!
>> PROBST: Timbira wins
immunity!
>> Somebody has to go tonight.
It's gotta be Spence.
>> PROBST: Fifth person voted
out of Survivor: Tocantins.
Tonight, a special episode of
Survivor, with new scenes
highlighting your favorite
contestants...
and giving deeper insight
into the game.
(theme song playing)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Enduring the intense
heat of the Brazilian highlands,
traveling on a dusty, endless
road to nowhere, this season's
castaways were split into two
tribes, and they were about to
begin a cutthroat game where
first impressions meant
everything.
>> Being in the back of that
truck really did give you a
good amount of time to just
kind of size everybody up and
see what you're up against.
>> As for first impressions
with people, I try not to come
into it with too many because
I think that gets you in trouble
a lot of times.
>> My first impression of the
girl in the gray striped
T-shirt, obviously, was upset;
she had her head down, and, yes,
it was hot, we were all hot, but
we weren't showing it.
And so, I really didn't feel
like she wanted to be here with
us.
>> It was blazing hot.
I had a fever.
I was so sick.
I didn't even give a flying
... what they thought
about me.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: You will have 60
seconds to gather as much as you
can.
Your time starts now because
this game is on!
>> Get down.
I'll hand it to you.
>> Here, hand it to me.
>> We have the long-haired guy
that, uh, looks like the love
child of Stephen Segal and the
last of the Mohicans.
So, if he can pull any of those
skills out, you know, survival
skills like an Indian or, uh,
karate moves like Stephen Segal,
he's a good guy to have on your
side, I think.
>> I plan on day one to take
the leadership role.
Now, is that going to be a
shared role?
It depends.
The characteristics and the
qualities that I have as an
individual has been forged like
an iron thrown into the fire and
coming out unshakable,
unbreakable, invincible like a
sword.
I know who I am.
>> We are screwed.
They have Stephen Segal.
What the hell are we going to
do against the (indistinct) man?
I have no idea.
We clearly have, physically, a
weaker tribe.
Um, there's the hot, blonde
girl.
It really is going to be a
shame when we have to vote her
off.
>> I guess I'm, you know, a
professional model now.
I mean, I've been doing it for
three and a half years, but, um,
yeah, I don't know, it's still
kind of funny to me because I
just, I laugh at myself a lot.
>> PROBST: You guys have a long
journey ahead of you.
You need to get to camp.
You need to start working on
shelter.
The tribes began an epic
four-hour journey toward their
camps, but Jalapao stumbled out
of the gate.
>> This was our mark, right?
I'm not afraid to run back to
the road and look at it.
>> I think that might be our
best point, our best idea.
>> You think so?
>> Yeah, I would definitely
because I'm not sure what tree
we're looking at.
>> As long as we don't veer off
that line, I know we do avoid
trees and stuff, it will still
be the same degree.
>> That's true.
That's true, all right.
>> If we just hit that strip
of palm trees, we'll be fine.
>> Well, J.T.'s, he's from 'Bama
>> That's right.
>> J.T. is more of a brawn guy,
not your sophisticate,
intellect, academia-type guy.
>> People's impression of me
might be that I'm a hillbilly
sometimes, uh, but I consider a
hillbilly someone uneducated.
I don't think a hillbilly would
make it very far in this game.
Uh, there's no doubt in my mind
I can win or I'd have stayed
at home.
I'm here to win and I'm going
to win.
>> Are we going the right way,
y'all?
My biggest strategy going in
will just be "kill them with
kindness."
I'll be so nice to them, they're
not going to want to kick me
off.
You guys okay?
Okay.
Because another thing I think
that they're probably
underestimating about me is
that I look fat.
But I'm not really fat.
I'm muscular.
So, when I'm winning challenges,
they won't have a reason to try
to kick me off.
They can't.
I'm going to be so good at this
they won't be ready for me.
>> Whoo!
(cheering)
(squealing)
>> Chew it! Chew it!
Don't waste it.
>> I guess it's like God's
candy.
>> Is this for real?
>> Thanks, God.
>> PROBST: On their first full
day at camp, but without fire to
cook their beans...
>> What happens if you just eat
dry beans?
>> PROBST: ...Timbira had to
resort to other sources of food
for much-needed protein.
>> Did you get it?
>> No.
>> I think it's going to be a
lot harder than anybody
realizes out here.
Foraging for food is going to be
difficult.
Dang.
>> I'm getting slower, I think.
Want to give it a try?
>> We're trying to catch fish.
We've got a burlap bag and
we try to drop different things
in and grab fish.
>> You got one?
>> Yes, a teeny little one.
>> At least it's one.
>> Eat it.
Eat that.
>> You go, you go, Debbie.
>> I'll eat that one that
you've got in your hands.
>> Why, because this guy...
>> Yeah, 'cause that one's
gross.
Ugh!
>> Put your mouth there.
>> Uh, okay.
>> Chew it! Chew it!
>> Chew it.
Don't just waste it.
Yummy, sushi, sashimi.
Mmm.
>> Okay, it actually did taste
a little like sushi.
That is definitely not in my
character, but I threw it in my
mouth and chewed it up as quick
as I could to get a little
protein.
I cannot believe I just chewed
up a live fish in my teeth.
>> I'm gonna clean these
things out.
>> The fish, we have just those
little minnows to eat, but we
found, uh, that fruit that
smells like foot.
>> Jerry!
>> Yeah.
>> All that jatoba.
Shut your mouth!
>> No, it's really, it's better
than eating the...
>> I'm having a hard time
sticking this in my mouth.
>> Come on. It's good.
>> This is a Brazilian fruit
called a jatoba, and, uh, it's
got like a really hard, like,
pod shell on it, and then inside
it's got this almost powdery
flesh.
It really makes you thirsty.
It kind of sucks all the saliva
out of your mouth.
>> Is this for real?
>> Yeah.
>> Come on. How is it?
>> Uh-uh.
>> But here, there's nothing
else to eat, so, it's, I guess
it's like God's candy in Brazil.
So, thanks, God.
>> PROBST: On day seven, after
winning comfort items in a
reward challenge, Jalapao's
campfire was out and getting the
fire restarted proved to be a
tough task.
(metal and wood scratching)
>> I'm doing something wrong
here.
>> Try to strike into it more.
>> Like that?
>> Strike it.
>> There you go.
>> Strike it. Like, hit it.
>> That's how I did it.
>> Stephen really wanted to
make a fire because he's never
made a fire.
He's out there with the flint,
with the machete, dinging away.
It was hilarious.
He could not make a freaking
spark.
>> On the scale of 1 to 100,
my wilderness skills are at
about a 1.
I cannot make fire, and that is
embarrassing.
Aah!
I'll do it some other time.
This is stupid.
>> Sure?
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> All right.
I might not be able to start
it, either.
(chuckles)
>> I grew up fishing with my
dad outdoors all the time, so
I've-I...
you know, I've lived the
outdoors.
I'm not just a girly girl, you
know.
I'm not just some pretty girl
that they're...
You know, they can flirt with.
(sighing)
>> Yes.
>> Good job, Syd.
>> Oh, nice, Sydney.
Fuego.
(chuckles)
>> At first, Sydney was
definitely getting by on her
looks, on her charm, on her
girlish laugh.
But Sydney made fire for us,
you know?
She's a woodland goddess and I
think, for that reason, she's a
big threat to me.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: At Timbira, Tyson was
busy enhancing the first
impression he'd made on his
fellow castaways, proving that
value to a tribe can come in
many ways.
>> I smell like a man today.
(laughing)
They think I just always smell
like flowers and exotic fruits.
Who am I?
Um...
Oh, that question.
Who am I?
Pretty well-balanced individual,
I'd say.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Let's win!
>> Oh, God.
(gasping)
>> Tyson never, ever ceases to
amaze me.
>> I can do that.
(laughing)
>> Oh, my God.
>> See?
>> Did you see the arch in his
back?
>> Yeah, you have to do the
arch.
It pops better.
>> I don't even know how to do
the arch thing.
Honestly, I think Tyson is
somebody that everybody better
watch out.
I think Tyson has the real
potential to win this game.
>> Try and get through this.
>> A little Tai Bo here, or
what?
Are you sparring?
What are you doing?
>> I was going to kick her in
the (bleep).
(laughing)
>> Tyson, he's always cracking
a joke.
One of a kind.
I mean, that's probably what
attracts me to him so much,
you know, not in a sexual way.
>> Take you to the ground right
here.
(laughing)
Ow.
>> What you doing, Debbie?
(laughing)
>> Debbie.
>> I want you to stop.
>> Stop doing that to me.
My parents are going to see
that, Debra!
>> You weren't very quick to
get off.
>> That is not lady-like.
>> I slipped and got stuck!
>> I don't know what you were
doing.
I was bent over looking at the
ground and you jumped right on
top.
Your boobs popped out?
>> Maybe.
>> That's fitting.
I'm not the stereotypical
Mormon.
I respect the church and the
people in it, but for myself,
personally, you know, there's
things I want to do and not
necessarily that are sinning.
>> Oh, no!
>> We'll see what happens when
I get home and everyone disowns
me.
Okay, team, I got tired of the
rope.
>> Oh, yeah, look at that.
(laughing)
>> Debbie!
>> Oh, my God.
>> You'll never be able to have
children again.
>> I don't care.
I'll probably have to move
somewhere else, somewhere less
Mormony.
>> Make beans?
I've always seen two people do
it.
>> Sierra, we've got to do
chores by ourselves.
We can't all hold each other's
hands.
>> Don't talk to me like I'm
stupid.
>> I'm just saying it doesn't
take two people.
I was not being condescending.
>>> I'm pissed.
>> How many handfuls of beans
should I do?
>> PROBST: Sierra made a bad
first impression with her
Timbira tribemates, but by day
eight, her strength seemed to
be returning and Coach was
ready to put her to work.
>> Sierra, how about you cook
the beans?
>> Make fire and the beans?
>> You'd have only one person
doing it.
One person putting the firewood
on the fire, same person cooking
the beans, and nobody stomping
around.
>> I've always seen two people
do it.
>> That's why we're getting
stuff in our beans and our
rice because there are too
many people around there.
I'm watching the stuff fly up
in the air while stuff is
cooking.
Sierra, you put a log on the
fire, then put another log on
the fire, and then stir the
beans, and then wait.
>> Yeah, I understand.
>> Put another log on the fire.
It doesn't take two people.
>> Don't talk to me like I'm
stupid.
>> I'm just saying it doesn't
take two people.
>> Yeah, but it's nice to have
someone, like a female, like
tending the fire and then one's
cooking and then...
You know what I mean?
It's nice to...
>> Sierra, we've got to do
chores by ourselves.
We can't all hold each other's
hands, and for to you say that
you want somebody there to talk
to, I mean, there's a lot of
stuff to do.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, we got to...
>> I know and I've been part
of it since day one.
>> I know that, but I'm
just saying we got to start
doing stuff independently, as
well.
>> Okay, that's fine.
What are you guys going to be
doing while I'm doing that?
>> Fishing.
>> All of you are going to go
fishing?
>> We're going to take about
four of us down there and
see if we can just surround
them and fish.
>> Okay.
>> Is that going to stress you
out?
It looks like it's stressing
you out.
>> Why don't you talk to me from
over here, so you don't get dirt
in the beans?
(chuckling)
I'm one of the ones working the
hardest, so...
I'm really getting tired of
people like Coach saying
things, "You need to do this,"
and shaking their finger and
coming down on me.
They think they can 'cause
they think they're older than me
and they think they're more
knowledgeable.
Um, it's only going to make me
turn on them faster.
>> I can be very condescending,
but as a leader or just as a
person, that's not somebody
that I want to be.
I was not being condescending
towards Sierra.
I was actually just trying to
wean her from the (bleep),
so to speak.
I don't think she's going to
fully realize her potential
when people keep coddling her.
There's a bunch of big, juicy
ones up there.
>> Uh-huh.
>> It's been a bountiful tree,
hasn't it been?
>> Yeah.
>> Not very talkative.
>> I'm pissed.
>> So, you want me to tell you
why I was picking on you?
>> Yeah.
>> I was gently trying to push
you out of the nest.
And I just...
I wanted to see you like,
expand yourself because I know
you can.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> You know, there's this part
of your personality that is
very dependent and there's this
part of your personality that's
very independent.
>> That's true.
>> Same as me.
But you can never coast in
life, in this game, and you
know that.
>> Now that I think about it
and start to, like, cool off,
I don't think Coach thinks I'm
stupid.
I think he has higher
expectations for me than he
does for other people.
He thinks of me as a strong
female.
You're going to be harder on
that one just so that they play
harder in a game.
And I think that's what...
where his mind's really at.
And I could very well be wrong,
but I think there's some good
intent behind it.
>> Thanks, Coach.
>> PROBST: Later that day, at
Jalapao, the muck and grime of
the game gave Sydney another
chance to prove her worth.
>> Look at this.
Is that a...
That is wild.
Nice.
Look at...
Looky here.
Birthmark there.
It is so dirty out here.
We live in ash, and it clings
to you.
>> Get away from me.
>> Every morning we get dirtier
and dirtier, so it's, um...
It's been kind of annoying for
us.
I mean, I'm totally down for a
floor.
And that would solve all of our
problem with the soot, with the
palms.
J.T. has had the plan to lift
our shelter off the ground, and
it's a good idea.
You know, why not try it?
And I wanted to show him that
I'm behind him 100%, and let's
just do it.
Let's go.
This is going to be awesome.
>> I don't think I'm the leader
of Jalapao.
I've just always been one where
I'm ready to get something done,
I do it myself.
So, I'm not doing it just to be
the leader or do anybody else
any favors.
I'm doing it because I want to
get it done, and that's the
best way to do something.
>> Wow.
>> Can I contribute here?
Is there anything I can do here?
Tying?
Digging?
Posting?
>> Uh...
>> I did think Stephen was
somewhat nerdy when we started
out.
It feels like I have a little
brother or sidekick.
He's definitely a city boy.
>> I think we're kind of going
along as we go, but we could
definitely use your help, yeah.
I think J.T. holds the power
right now.
So I'm definitely trying to get
on his good side a little bit.
I think people have their first
impressions of me, and, you
know, and I always try to prove
that wrong.
I think we did a really good
job on... on, you know, getting
the floor off the ground.
I'll sleep better tonight.
That's for sure.
(thunder rumbling)
>> PROBST: The battle for tribe
leader had been ongoing between
Brendan and Coach at Timbira,
and on day eight, they went
toe-to-toe to provide comfort
for the tribe.
>> Hey, Coach, when you do
the seat...
>> Yes.
>> ...can you... any chance you
could put ropes in between it?
I think it's more comfortable...
>> I was actually going to put
three together.
>> Oh, put three together.
>> I was going to put three
together.
>> But it's got to be
comfortable this time.
>> The thing is, is that every
time I make another seat around
here, everybody uses it and I
don't even get it use my own
seat.
>> Well, you're making it for
the good...
making your own personal seat.
>> No, I'm not!
I'm just saying...
>> No.
>> I would love something to do.
>> Give me some twine.
I'll undo the twine.
>> A bench-making contest?
>> Yes.
>> Ooh, I love to see the alpha
men go at it.
>> Coach is definitely a
character.
We're competing here and there
but to me, this is about having
a good time.
That's what we came out here to
do, and so any time, you know,
you're not, you should kind of
check yourself and be like,
let's do it.
>> Coach needs it more than I
do.
>> I've got longer rope.
Funky.
>> There is a very serious vying
for the spot of alpha male
contest happening right now.
I don't think it has anything to
do with benches or swings or
seats.
I think it's who can come out
on top, as usual.
>> Put your ass going in between
the two.
>> That's even worse.
>> Oh, please.
>> This is terrible, man!
>> Tearing the tribe apart,
guys.
>> The ladies will come over
and judge.
>> So we're having a bench-
building contest, which we love.
Because now we have more places
to sit.
>> Now we have more seats.
And what my idea is, like, let's
start having contests of who can
get the river water faster.
>> All the time, yeah.
>> Who can get the beans going
the fastest.
>> Who can collect the most
firewood?
We'll judge them all.
It will be great.
>> Oh, see, I can't leave that.
>> Oh, this is very comfortable!
(Tarzan yell)
>> I haven't sat on that one
yet.
>> That's definitely going
to be more comfortable.
>> Yeah, and we said that it
was only about comfort, man.
It was not about time.
It was not about people.
>> It was about taking care of
the tribe.
>> Yeah, I think I know where
Coach's button is.
>> We did not say it.
>> Coach, it's not about you.
It's about the tribe.
>> I know it's about the tribe.
Why do you think I wanted to
have a bench-building contest
in the first place?
>> This is the most fun I've had
in a while.
I'm an entrepreneur, so I
started a business.
When I think about business,
you know, every day, when you
build something from scratch,
interacting with people that
you've never met before is
something I adore.
You know, Coach tries to act
like a coach all the time.
We're not out here to have a
coach.
We don't need one.
You know, we're out here to have
friends; we're out here to work
with people.
>> 'Cause it will fall down
when you sit on it.
>> This is delicious.
Good job.
>> That was good.
>> PROBST: At Jalapao, Taj, used
to a high standard of living
back home, was having a hard
time adjusting to the elements.
>> Your back is really, really
bad.
>> Yeah.
I can't believe I look like
this.
I feel like a leper.
>> How are you feeling?
Are you all right?
>> No, I'm fine.
>> No, you can come on.
We're just... I'm chitchatting
with her, man.
I know she had a...
>> I can't look at myself.
>> I just feel so ugly.
>> It must have been really hard
last night.
>> Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
(sobbing)
>> I got a little emotional
because I just looked at
myself...
and I just had a moment
because I just... I don't know
what's going on.
My back is just destroyed.
And I still have to go home.
So I just don't want to go home
looking like a wreck.
>> One of the hardest things
you've ever done?
>> You know, it wasn't so much
hard.
I swear, I can handle this.
It's just the after-effect
looking at myself.
I'm just like, "Ew!"
What am I doing to myself?
What am I doing?
>> To my body, yeah.
>> I never felt so ugly before
in my life.
Stephen came down and he talked
to me and they made me feel
better, but...
I'm just having a moment.
Everyone has their moments out
here, and today is mine.
I'm just more determined now.
I cannot go home empty-handed
looking like this.
(laughs)
>> I thought I saw a snake
going through the rafters.
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Oh!
>> Coach-- just the biggest joke
on the planet.
>> PROBST: After a restless
night of sleep, on morning ten,
Timbira was still making
discoveries about the dangers of
their environment.
>> I heard something about a
snake, too.
>> It was a nightmare, a
flashback from when I was on the
Amazon and a snake wrapped
around my neck.
I was having that nightmare
sometimes; it's reoccurring.
(indistinct audio)
>> That's okay.
I was just like, well...
>> It's one thing to have that
dream at home and talking in
your sleep, but when...
>> When it could happen here.
>> Last night, Coach woke up
and screamed, "Snake."
Well, we thought he was dreaming
and being silly or whatever.
Oh, my gosh!
Okay, has anybody else seen
this?
>> What?
>> That is a snake skin.
>> Oh, gross.
>> This wasn't here yesterday.
Oh, my gosh!
A snake has shed his skin
right here.
Brendan, come see what we found.
>> I told you I saw a snake in
there last night, man.
>> I thought you were you were
dreaming about it.
>> Maybe it wasn't a dream.
>> Oh, my God!
>> I swear, man, I looked up
and I thought I saw a snake
going through the rafters.
>> Really?
>> I'm not kidding.
But then I thought it was my
reoccurring dream of being in
the Amazon.
>> They're not going to just
come up and bite us while we're
sleeping, would they?
>> They could.
>> Okay, this is really freaky.
We really got to be careful
out here.
This place is infested with
snakes, with nasty, poisonous
snakes.
So I'm being very careful as to
where I step.
>> Hey, we're in the wild.
That's what happens.
We're part of their environment.
>> That just really bums me out.
>> PROBST: While over at
Jalapao...
...J.T. and Joe enjoyed some
good, sporting fun.
Though it didn't stop Joe from
thinking about the game.
>> A little jatoba ball.
>> Oh!
Right now, it's probably J.T.
leading Jalapao.
And I don't think there's a lot
of tension between J.T.
and I right now.
>> Oh!
You brought the heat.
>> It's kind of nice to have
somebody you can just let take
over and then also, you know,
the spotlight isn't on you.
>> Take a little saliva off
that ball.
Maybe it will fly straight.
>> That's at least a triple.
>> My kind of ace in the hole,
as compared to J.T.,
is going to be my strategy and
kind of my social game moving
forward.
>> All right, here you go.
Single.
>> Is that all?
>> That was it.
He's more of the basic just
kind of provider, you know,
kind of just alpha male type of
guy.
>> A little fungo.
>> Oh!
Oh, dude. Ow.
>> Right back at ya.
You tried to get me off the
plate.
My bad.
>> Oh, that's gone.
>> What in the hell?
>> I'd imagine that as we go
further on in the game, it will
get a little tense, and, you
know, that's something that I'm
prepared for.
I know that's going to happen.
>> We better quit or we'll lose
an eye.
>> I think I won, dude.
(sighs)
>> PROBST: After two visits to
Tribal Council, spirits were
down at Timbira, so Coach called
upon his conducting skills to
orchestrate some smiles.
>> Tonight we're gonna play
Peter Tchaikovsky's "March
Slav," and it goes like this.
>> Okay.
(humming lively melody)
(voice deepens, continues
singing)
And then I cue the strings.
Ready and...
(singing minor-key melody)
And that means I want a little
crescendo and then a
decrescendo.
(continues minor-key melody)
(continues singing melody)
>> Who is this jackass?
(singing melody)
Coach-- just the biggest
joke on the planet.
Like, I'm in a weird position
because I don't really like my
tribe all that much.
And I don't have the alliances
out here, but I think it would
be kind of fun to pretend for a
while, like, "We are one big
happy family!
We're in love.
Everything's great."
You know, every time I get a
couple more days out here, it's
that much closer to a merge.
If I can make it that far, it'll
be interesting to see how it
plays out.
(whooping)
>> Bravo! Bravo!
(wind whistling)
(thunder rumbling)
>> I have never been so close to
another man.
What is that?
>> You're solid, right?
>> Yes, dude.
>> I'll never vote you out.
>> I don't perceive him as being
near the player that I am.
>> We have two immunity idols.
We have the control.
>> But is he entirely
trustworthy?
(thunder rumbles)
Maybe he's not.
>> PROBST: On day 13, Coach and
Tyson took advantage of an early
morning walk to make some
long-term plans.
I think that, uh, we get rid of
Erinn 'cause she's a cancer.
>> Here's the thing.
We can use... we can use Erinn
for a few votes.
She'll stick with us for that
long.
>> Oh, no. I hate doing that.
I hate doing that, and I don't
trust her.
A lot of people don't want to
talk about who's gonna be
eliminated.
Tyson and I-- we're thinking
about it every day.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm gonna tell you this.
I told you from the first day,
I'll never vote you out.
>> Yeah.
>> And I'm telling you right
now, man to man, I'll never go
back on that.
>> Yeah, me, neither.
>> Like I told you, you're the
most popular guy in this tribe.
You'll be the most popular guy
in this game.
I ruffle people's feathers.
You know, that's just me.
>> Yeah.
>> You say the same thing that I
do, and everybody laughs.
I say what you say, and
everybody's, like, "Whoa!
That was wrong."
I mean, I-I just wanted to just
let you know that.
>> Yeah. I'm the same way.
>> Okay.
Coach. He's the coach, you know?
Right now I'm mostly agreeing
with what he says.
But in this game, I... don't
perceive him as being near the
player that I am.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: While across the
river at Jalapao, J.T. and
Stephen were also discussing the
future of the game.
>> I-I feel confident that we
could now try to find some
divisions.
There are four of us;
we could find two of them.
>> I do like having Stephen
around.
I mean, he's just from such a
different part of the world, and
it's hard to imagine we'd ever
been friends otherwise.
But I know we'll always be
friends now.
I think you should lay 'em there
and go down there and check it
out.
>> J.T. and I have formed a
bond.
I'm excited to be his friend.
He is the likeable Everyman with
the sweet Southern drawl and the
charming smile.
>> Now, lay down on your belly
right there.
>> He's showing me how to fish,
how to tie a line.
I think he thinks of me as sort
of his sidekick, but is J.T.
entirely trustworthy?
Maybe he's not.
I mean, you're solid, right?
>> Yes, dude.
>> Yeah, okay, me, too.
>> No doubt.
I'm solid with you.
And then we go to the merge,
then we start looking towards
the final... final three.
>> Final three. That's it.
>> And then, if I win, I take
you.
You win, you take me?
We go to final two.
That'd be awesome.
>> J.T. has definitely emerged
as our tribe leader, and, um, I
hope to put myself into a power
position.
But I'm not the strongest
physical competitor, and so I
need to be with J.T. as much as
possible.
Things are definitely improving
for me in this game, but I know
better than to, you know, say
that with certainty.
>> PROBST: Later that day,
Brendan chose Stephen to join
him at Exile...
hoping to put in place the final
piece of his Exile alliance with
Sierra and Taj.
>> Whoa, that's enormous.
>> That's big, man.
>> Oh, that's kind of
disgusting, actually.
How tall?
What, three, four feet?
>> Yeah, and there's some that
fell off down there.
>> Oh, man.
>> Here.
It'll be a good boa for you.
>> A little, uh, a little
decoration?
Oh, thank you.
>> There you go.
>> I feel pretty, finally.
>> When I came out to Exile this
time, um, I wanted Stephen's
trust.
I think Stephen didn't
necessarily believe all this was
going on, didn't know me, didn't
know Sierra, and so I think it's
important that the four of us
trust each other and know that
we're going to the finals
together.
Are you guys solid in your
tribe?
Like, there's no fear of you
getting eliminated?
>> I don't think so.
I mean, we thought Erinn might
be on the outs.
>> Yeah.
I needed to be very honest with
him, and so I tried to tell him
as much as could about my tribe,
about how we could work
together, just to make him feel
comfortable with that alliance.
All right, you ready?
>> Mm-hmm.
Damn, you're quite the woodman.
(thunder rumbling)
>> Oh, come on, dude.
Who's doing this?
>> Oh, no!
>> (laughs): Are you serious?
(thunder rumbling)
I have never been so close to
another man.
He and I spooned for all we were
worth.
Oh, my God, it was raining.
It was cold.
Nothing could prepare me for
lying huddled against, you know,
a hunk of-of man.
(thunder rumbles)
>> I'm exhausted. I'm...
>> Um, the night Steve and I had
out here on Exile was probably
the worst night I've had, and so
we huddled up and spooned all
night and had a great bonding
experience.
Another 20 minutes?
What do we got here?
>> It's actually coming over the
mountain, a little bit.
>> Ah, there it is.
>> Ah, feels good, doesn't it?
>> Yeah.
And that's the one really cool
thing about Exile: it's just a
bonding experience far greater
than what... than could happen
back at our tribes.
Look how long our shadows are.
>> Oh, God.
>> Uh... what kind of shapes
can you make?
(laughs)
>> What I love about our group
is we have a four-person
alliance: you have myself;
you have Sierra;
you have Taj and Stephen;
and we're all, like,
it's, like, it's kind of a
motley crew.
We have two immunity idols.
We have the control, and, you
know, hopefully, it'll be
smooth sailing from there.
Can you make a... I guess, a
"T"?
>> A cross, yeah.
>> "H."
Sort of.
>> I've just met Brendan.
We've bonded because we have...
we have spooned quite a bit.
And I'm glad right now that I'm
in his alliance.
But there's a lot that's going
on in my tribe right now, and my
priority has to be to make sure
that I get to the merge in a
really strong place.
>> No more cuddling once we get
back to the merge tribe, yeah.
>> Much as I would love to.
(laughs): Yeah.
>> PROBST: 11 castaways are
left.
Of the first five votes,
three have been blindsides.
What will happen when the
challenges get more intense...
the rewards bigger...
the stakes higher?
>> You are such a liar!
>> PROBST: Will friendships and
alliances that formed early
continue through the game?
And what twists await?
(yelling)
>> PROBST: Join us next time...
as the adventure continues.
(bird screeches)
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Timbira turns on Coach.
>> We all were frustrated with
Coach.
>> And the truth shall set you
free!
>> PROBST: And at Jalapao...
>> We're going to merge.
>> We're going to the end.
>> PROBST: ...the tribe turns on
each other.
>> It's terrible.
I'm going to hell.
>> Remember when you kind of...
>> Yeah.
>> ...when you wouldn't stop?
>> Yeah, I remember.
When can we do it again?
>> You'd probably have to give
me, like, ten minutes or
something.
>> Ten minutes in between?
>> Yep.
>> You're a stud.
>> I know.
I can go all night.
(laughs)