>> PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
This game is on.
Timbira had the early advantage
when they outmaneuvered Jalapao
in the game's opening moments.
>> We got all the water, we got
all the beans, everything we
needed.
>> PROBST: And Timbira
continued to dominate when they
won the first immunity
challenge.
Carolina, the tribe has spoken.
At Exile Island, Taj and
Brendan formed a secret
cross-tribal alliance...
(Taj laughs)
...with plans to include Taj's
Jalapao tribe mate Stephen and
Brendan's Timbira tribe mate
Sierra.
(thunder rumbles)
(cheering)
Jalapao won the next immunity
challenge, sending Timbira to
Tribal Council.
Candace, the tribe has spoken.
Jalapao wins immunity!
Jalapao then went on to gain a
clear advantage.
Timbira, another tribe member
going home.
Timbira tried to solve their
problems by choosing a leader.
>> I think it should be Brendan.
>> PROBST: Which angered Coach,
who thought he was in charge.
>> I love to be the leader.
That's what I'm used to doing.
>> PROBST: Erinn disagreed.
>> I think it's a role that
Coach is used to, but it's
something that Brendan does
better.
>> PROBST: Erinn.
Erinn's conflict with Coach
almost got her voted out.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins: Jerry.
But Jerry was sent home for
being weakened by his illness...
The tribe has spoken.
...putting Timbira at six
members to Jalapao's seven.
Can Timbira put aside their
differences to make a comeback?
13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(Debbie sighs)
>> Uh, so at Tribal Council
tonight, Erinn and I got into an
argument about the leadership
on the tribe.
And she said Brendan is a
better leader.
But she doesn't know what she's
talking about.
It pissed me off, and it made me
think Erinn's got to go because
she is the cancer of the tribe.
She would have been voted out
tonight, almost unanimously,
had it not been for Jerry
coming down sick.
>> You guys, you want to do a
powwow?
>> I thought it was actually
great last night that, like,
Jeff brought it up.
>> I mean, we could have a
general leader.
>> If we all decide that Coach
wants to do it or Tyson wants
to do it, I'm totally on board.
So I think we just kind of
all, just as a group, kind
of decide what we think works
best, and then just make that
decision and be done with it.
>> Right.
>> We need it.
It's crazy.
It's crazy not to have it.
>> Last night at Tribal, we
established a leader, kind of.
So I guess Brendan or Coach is
the leader.
I don't know.
It's, uh... I wasn't paying
attention.
I don't really care.
>> I think that... as much as I
like leading, and, you know, if
you were voted off tomorrow,
yeah, I'd gladly step into that
role.
But I think that, at the
moment, everybody, including
myself, trusts you as being the
leader.
And as much as I would enjoy
that role, we just have that one
person.
>> Yeah.
>> It's more productive.
>> You know, if Brendan got
voted off and I was the leader,
I think this tribe would be
better.
But I don't want to vote
Brendan off because that's my
M.O.
I want iron that sharpens iron.
>> And I didn't mean to sound
last night like I was saying I
don't think that you would be a
good leader.
I think you would be a great
leader.
>> There's only one experienced
person out here as far as being
out in the outdoors, and that
would be me.
These people here are new kids
on the block.
What they've been doing is
not succeeding, not thriving,
but existing.
If you look at me, you look at
Brendan, who looks stronger?
I do.
We need to thrive in the wild
and not just exist.
And I think the difference is
is that I've been here, and they
haven't.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> When Taj goes to Exile, I
think we're all concerned with
how she's holding up.
It's definitely worn her down
to be out there and to be out
in the elements with no food,
no water, nobody to trust.
So we're all concerned with
the toll this is going to take
on her in the long run.
>> I am.
>> Brendan and I have our
secret Exile alliance.
So now I need to talk to
Stephen because I know I can
trust him.
He's kind of like the nerdy,
shy guy who just wants to help
everybody, and I know that I can
depend on him in the long run.
>> How you feeling?
>> This hammock feels lovely.
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> You look quite relaxed in
there.
>> Thank you.
When you get a second, I want
to talk to you by yourself,
okay?
>> Yeah, absolutely.
(hooting)
>> All right, this is the deal.
This is going to change your
life, okay?
Do you want to be a part of the
biggest upset on Survivor
history?
>> Yes, I do.
>> Okay.
He's in an alliance with
Sierra, and I told him about
you.
So the next...
>> Taj apparently is aligned
with Brendan and Sierra in the
other tribe.
They made a pact on Exile
Island to stick with each
other, stay in the game as long
as we can, and look out for each
other once we get to the merge.
So I might have just stumbled
ass-backwards into a huge
alliance.
>> So the next time we go to a
challenge, if we win, we choose
Sierra.
>> Okay.
>> Sierra's going to choose you.
>> You're selling me Exile
Island, isn't that tough?
>> It's not bad at all.
(laughter)
I'm telling you...
I will protect you.
I will make sure you're fine.
I just need you to roll with us.
>> We got tree mail.
It's a sandbag.
>> Oh, gosh!
>> "As time ticks away,
supplies start to dwindle.
Your spirits may begin to
corrode.
For a boost in morale and
improvements at camp, you must
know who can shoulder the load."
(Coach laughs)
>> That means someone's going
to Exile for two days.
>> I just want to win the
reward.
>> Yeah.
>> Who do you want us to pick
if we win?
You want us to go with Taj
again?
>> I think we go Taj.
>> And then she's going to get
to say you.
>> When Taj and I were on
Exile, we set up the Exile
alliance-- me with Sierra, and
Taj with Stephen.
But I didn't communicate that I
had the alliance yet because I
hadn't had a chance to talk to
Sierra yet.
So she doesn't know about the
plan, and it could be a pretty
heinous situation.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Jalapao getting your first look
at the new Timbira tribe.
Jerry voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, three members of
each tribe will have a pole
across their shoulders.
Each round, weight will be
added to that pole.
The decision about which tribe
member gets the weight will be
made by two members of the
other tribe.
When the weight becomes too
much, you'll drop your pole,
you're out of the challenge.
Last person left standing wins
reward for their tribe.
Only rule in this challenge:
you must put two men and one
woman as your weight bearers--
those holding the pole.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Today, the reward is
a camp raid.
The winning tribe will send two
members over to the camp of the
losing tribe, where you will be
allowed to steal two items.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will choose one
member from the losing tribe to
go to Exile Island.
That person will in turn select
somebody from the winning tribe
to join them.
Worth playing for?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Because today's
challenge only requires five
people, each tribe will sit
people out.
Timbira, you have one extra
member.
Who you going to sit out?
>> Sierra.
>> PROBST: Jalapao, you're
sitting out two people.
>> Steve and I are sitting out.
>> PROBST: Stephen, Spencer,
Sierra, take a spot on the
sit-out bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize, and we'll
get started.
All right, the weight bearers
for Jalapao: Joe, Taj, J.T.
For Timbira: Debra, Brendan, and
Tyson.
Last person left standing wins
reward for their tribe.
Let's get started.
Jalapao, who you want to put
the weight on first?
>> Brendan.
>> PROBST: Timbira?
>> Joe.
>> PROBST: Put the weight on.
Each tribe will put the weight
on their own tribe member to
make sure it is placed evenly,
but the other tribe decides who
actually gets it.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Put the weight on.
Each bag weighs ten pounds.
So each round, you are adding
20 pounds.
Next round.
Timbira, who you want on?
>> J.T.
>> PROBST: J.T. getting some
weight.
>> Tyson.
>> PROBST: Tyson.
Put it on.
Spreading the weight around.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Release.
Jalapao, who you want to put it
on?
Brendan.
>> PROBST: Brendan getting more
weight.
>> Taj.
>> PROBST: Taj getting some
weight. Put it on.
Brendan getting two more bags.
That'll put him up to 40 pounds.
Taj getting into on the action
with her first 20 pounds.
This is about endurance and
strategy.
How long can you stand the
weight?
Who do you give it to?
♪ ♪
Brendan now at 180 pounds.
J.T. at 160, Tyson at 120.
Joe at 140.
Taj and Debra both holding
strong at 80 pounds.
Next round.
>> Brendan.
>> PROBST: Brendan getting more
weight.
>> J.T.
>> PROBST: Puts J.T. at 180.
This will put Brendan up to 200.
>> Come on, man, come on.
>> PROBST: The record in this
challenge: 220 pounds.
Survivor: Pearl Islands:
a man with a beard, Rupert.
Brendan is two bags away from
that.
Next round.
>> J.T.
>> Brendan.
>> PROBST: Do it.
J.T. and Brendan both getting
more weight.
>> Brendan's wobbling.
>> PROBST: This'll put Brendan
up to 220.
>> He's wobbling.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Brendan drops out
just as the weight goes on.
Brendan out of the challenge.
>> Whoa!
>> You got this.
You got it, buddy. You got it.
Yes, J.T.
>> Come on, J.T.
>> PROBST: J.T. now at 200
pounds for Jalapao.
Timbira now down to Tyson and
Debra to win it for them.
Jalapao holding strong with all
three tribe members still in it.
>> Attaboy, Jet.
You got this.
>> PROBST: Next round.
>> J.T.
>> Tyson.
>> PROBST: This will put Tyson
at 140 pounds.
J.T. at 220 pounds.
>> Damn, J.T., this is it.
>> Hold it, buddy, hold it.
>> This is a record, man.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one,
drop.
>> Attaboy.
Attaboy, Jet.
>> Yeah! Whoo!
>> Yeah, J.T.!
>> Strongest man alive!
>> PROBST: Tyson drops out at
140.
>> As long as you can, Jet.
>> PROBST: Jalapao's strategy is
working.
They've eliminated both men.
Debra, the last remaining member
of Timbira in this challenge.
>> Yeah, J.T.
>> PROBST: J.T. drops out after
holding 220 pounds, tying
Rupert's record from the Pearl
Islands.
Joe at 140.
Taj at 80.
Joe drops out right behind J.T.!
>> Taj, hang in there, baby.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Suddenly, this
challenge has come down to the
women.
>> All right, little mommy.
>> PROBST: Wow, just like that,
this challenge has flipped on
its head.
Jalapao had a huge lead and is
now down to Taj for Jalapao...
>> It's all you, girl.
>> PROBST: ...Debra for Timbira.
Both women at 80 pounds.
Let's put on some more weight.
No choices to be made.
You know who's getting it.
>> That's just what we wanted
to happen.
You and her.
>> PROBST: This will put both
women at a hundred pounds.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Drop.
Deborah at a hundred pounds.
Taj at a hundred pounds.
>> Taj, you are solid, baby.
>> We need you, T.
>> PROBST: Last person left
standing wins reward, which is
a camp raid.
Let's put on some more weight.
Both women at a hundred pounds.
Going to move it up to 120.
>> Come on, Tajie.
>> Stay firm, T.
>> It's sliding. It's sliding.
>> Yeah!
(cheering)
>> PROBST: Debra drops out.
Jalapao wins reward!
(cheering)
>> That's all right, Debra.
You did a hell of a job, girl.
You did a hell of a job.
>> Thank you.
>> Hey, that's all hard, baby.
Good job.
>> PROBST: Jalapao with your
fourth straight win in a row.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Nice job.
Decision: who from Timbira
are you going to send to Exile
Island?
>> Let's send Sierra.
Let's see how she likes it.
>> Good 'cause I'm taking you.
>> Oh, you witch!
>> PROBST: Sierra's picking Taj.
All right.
>> That's all right.
I'm used to it now.
>> Today, I didn't have a chance
to speak with Sierra before the
challenge, so I'm glad she just
picked Taj, which was good.
I hope Taj will be able to
explain enough about the
situation to hopefully work
things out.
>> We love you, Taj.
>> PROBST: Both Sierra and Taj
will be back in time for the
next immunity challenge.
Timbira, nothing for you.
Head back to camp.
Two members from Jalapao will
be showing up to do a little
shopping.
>> Good job, you guys.
>> Good job.
>> You did awesome.
>> Nice.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Jalapao on your way
back, choose two members to
raid Timbira.
Grab your stuff.
Head out.
>> Good job, baby.
>> My biggest concern when we
lost the challenge today is
they're going to clean out our
food supply, and then we're
going to go downhill.
We're going to be nothing as
a tribe in another three, four
days with these people only
eating rice.
>> You guys did a great job
today.
>> Yeah, you guys did so good.
>> Yeah, totally.
>> Do you think they're going
to take both bean bags or just
one and one rice?
>> But if they can take two
things, we really don't have
anything here of value besides
the beans.
>> Yes, we do.
We have the water cans.
We get back to camp and we know
that there's two people on
their way over from Jalapao
to raid our camp, take whatever
they want.
And we know they're after the
beans.
So all we're thinking is what
else could we convince them
that they should take?
(applause)
>> Welcome to our abode.
>> Y'all got a pretty place
here.
>> Nice.
>> Hey!
>> Tyson, good job.
>> You, too, man.
>> Good game, man.
>> It felt a little weird
having those two guys from the
other tribe come in.
>> Could we get you a cocktail?
>> Yeah, if you don't mind.
>> You want to be on good terms
with them 'cause you're probably
going to be living with them in
the future, but in the back of
your mind, you're like, "I want
to punch these guys in the
head."
>> Well, maybe we could, uh, use
a little way around the store,
tell us which aisle it's on
or something.
>> All right.
>> Oh, no, you go find it.
>> We know y'all got some extra
food.
We've been living on rice.
>> I'd be careful what you take.
Just remember, you may end up
over here sometime.
>> Oh, I know.
We're not going to leave you
without food.
>> You know we have watering
cans over here.
We hear you're boiling water.
>> We might as well just take
a sack of beans and something
else.
>> That's what I'm thinking.
Take that sack; leave this.
>> Thanks.
>> We're not going to take the
rest of their beans, so we might
as well just take this.
I think it's a very smart idea
not to take both sacks of beans
because you have to look forward
in this game.
There could be a switch at any
time.
And if I was to end up over
there on the Timbira Tribe with
no beans 'cause I just stole
both sacks, I'd be pissed.
>> Okay.
>> All right, y'all.
>> Bye, Santa Claus.
>> We'll see you guys.
>> See you guys.
>> Thanks a lot.
>> Thank you.
>> Whoa! Hello!
>> Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
>> Welcome back.
>> It's good to be back, y'all.
>> Who wants some beans?
>> Oh, my God!
What do you got?
>> All right, so the real deal,
though, is they had two bags of
beans.
>> Yeah.
>> One smaller bag...
>> One, this is the bigger one.
>> You left their bag of beans?
>> We left a bag of beans.
>> We left their smaller bag.
>> But why do you want to leave
them food?
>> In case we switch or
anything.
>> Yeah.
>> They're probably thankful to
you all that you just took a bag
of beans.
>> Oh, yeah.
We didn't take nothing from
them.
They still got beans, and they
still got water containers.
But, you know, there was nothing
else to take.
>> You know, if they're thinking
strategy, I don't think it's the
right strategy.
You know, it's just, it's like
you've got a hundred guns, let's
take 75 of them.
You can have 25, oh, and maybe
be able to take a shot at us.
>> Oh, my God.
This is the happiest day of
my life.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's just pig out.
>> What are they, pinto beans?
>> Mixture.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, beans, just beans?
Black beans? White beans?
>> And pinto, I think.
>> They are farting beans.
(Sandy laughing)
They are farting beans, honey.
>> Sandy's kind of starting to
get on my nerves, as crazy as
she is.
She repeats everything at least
three times.
And it's starting to, I think,
wear on everybody, and not just
me.
>> I did! You are always...
>> I'm going to smack you.
>> No, isn't that true?
It's always, I'm the one that's
like, "Oh, no," this, that and
the other, and there you go.
But, anyway, y'all just do
whatever you want.
>> Oh, wow.
Look at this.
>> Thank the Lord for the beans.
>> If I were choosing who was
leaving this tribe next...
it would be Sydney.
Sydney is using everything she
has from head to toe to enchant
every one of the boys.
She runs around in their boxers
and then, you know, doesn't
sleep in her bra at night.
And she is, like, up against
the boys 24/7.
Trust me, she's playing this
game hard and, uh, it's working.
Oh, they love her to death.
I still think they can see
through it, but they still like
the package, you know?
They're going to put your name
down there, you better do
something.
You better be pulling off more
than a bra.
You better be pulling some
panties off or something.
(laughing)
Oh, you know, so I might have to
trick her that way.
(laughs)
If I can't outwit her with the
body, I'll outwit her with the
brain.
>> All right, choose an urn.
>> See if it has anything in it.
Usually, one of them does;
one of them doesn't.
Nothing's in there?
Yup, I got the clue.
Open in private.
All right, I'll be right back.
"Every day or two, you get mail
from this place.
If you find it round here,
you'll ask, 'Why the long
face?'"
Tree mail, I knew it.
I knew it was the tree mail.
>> Once Sierra and I arrived at
Exile, we chose urns, and I got
lucky and chose the one with
the clue in it.
It's exactly where I thought it
would be.
It's back at my home camp at
tree mail.
When Brendan got back, he didn't
didn't talk to you about himself
at all?
>> No.
>> Not one second?
Hmm... okay.
I was kind of talking to Sierra
down the road, trying to see
where her head was at, and,
apparently, Brendan had never
had a chance to fill her in on
the plan.
So I'll have to fill her in on
everything.
Okay, well, here's the deal.
No one knows that you and
Brendan are cool on your side,
and no one knows that Steve and
I are cool on my side.
Once we get the two idols, we
basically have security through
the merge.
And once we get to the merge,
we'll have a secret four-way
alliance that no one knows about
and can't break up.
This way, we can watch each
others' backs when somebody's
trying to blindside one of us.
We can warn them.
We can take other people out
without them even knowing it.
>> This is awesome.
This is an absolutely amazing
plan.
It just feels great that I built
an alliance with Brendan,
that I chose the right person
who was smart enough to form an
alliance to create this awesome
foursome, ruling all the idols.
I started at the bottom of the
food chain.
I climbed my way to the middle,
and now I'm at the top, baby.
>> Our concern is getting to
the final four, which will be
you, me, Steve, and Brendan.
Are you game?
>> I'm game, game.
>> Rock on.
>> I'm game.
>> All right.
Team Secret is in place.
>> It's amazing.
>> Is there anything that we
should do today?
>> Hmm... rest?
Eat, drink, and be merry.
>> That sounds great.
>> Yeah.
>> I'd love to do that.
>> I've been laying in the
water.
>> Today is just a relaxation,
fun day.
We're just kind of enjoying not
having a lot of work to do.
We needed to play, laugh, and
have a little bit of fun
because if you start getting
down out here, all the different
doors start opening: I miss my
family; I miss my husband;
I miss my children.
You know, and so we've got to
keep each other up.
>> I'm going tribal all over
everybody's asses.
>> Dude, this is insane, man.
>> Oh, my God!
>> This is insane!
>> Look at how ripe a tan I'm
going to get on my ass cheeks
now.
I made this myself.
>> You are the man.
This is hilarious.
>> Imagine if I single-handedly
bring the loincloth back to
civilized society.
(laughing)
>> I can't breathe!
I can't breathe.
>> I said a-bunga, unga-bunga,
unga-bunga, unga-bunga.
(laughing)
>> Oh, my God!
>> I don't know what it is, but
I'm having a tough time finding
a connection with these people.
Before I came out here, I went
through a really terrible
breakup.
I can't even carry on normal
conversations with people
anymore.
It makes it hard to talk about
everything because it's going
to come up, and I don't...
(voice breaking): This is what
happens when it comes up.
And I don't want to do this out
here.
>> For the most part, I've
written Erinn off.
I mean, I haven't really talked
to her one-on-one about
anything.
And she doesn't hang out with
the tribe a lot.
Plus, I think she'll be really,
really upset when she gets
voted off, and I'd like to see
a freak-out at Tribal.
I think that'll be fun.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
We'll now bring in Taj and
Sierra, returning from Exile
Island.
>> Come on in, girl.
>> We missed you, sweetie.
>> Missed you.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first.
Give it up, Sydney.
>> All right, all right.
>> PROBST: Let's get to today's
challenge.
One tribe member at a time will
race out, retrieve a puzzle
piece... race back.
Then, the next person goes.
Once you've collected all eight
pieces, you must place them in
their correct spot in the frame
and rotate them to reveal the
winning phrase.
First tribe to get it right
wins immunity, is safe at least
one more day in this game.
Losers go to Tribal Council.
Another person will be voted
out.
Jalapao, you have one extra
member for this challenge.
Who's sitting out this one?
>> I can't run.
>> You can't run.
>> Let her sit out.
>> Taj is sitting out.
>> PROBST: Taj will take a spot
on the bench.
Everybody else, we'll get
started.
Here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
You must untie.
Then, the piece will drop; then
you unclip it and race back.
>> Yeah, Joe!
>> Come on!
Whoo!
>> Good, Joe! Nice!
>> Joe-Joe!
>> PROBST: J.T. on the course
for Jalapao.
Erinn now on the course for
Timbira.
>> Come on, J.T.!
>> PROBST: J.T. whips through
those knots.
He's heading back now with
Jalapao's second puzzle piece.
Erinn has hers down quickly.
Spencer on the course.
>> Take your time, Erinn!
>> PROBST: Brendan now out on
the course for Timbira.
Spencer has the third piece.
>> Yeah, Spencer!
>> PROBST: Brendan heading back
for Timbira.
>> Come on, Brendan!
>> Let's go, Spence!
>> Yeah, Spence.
>> PROBST: Stephen now out on
the course for Jalapao.
>> Good job, Brendan!
Good job, Brendan.
>> PROBST: Tyson out on the
course.
>> Let's go, Steve-o!
>> Yeah, Stephen!
>> PROBST: Stephen has the
fourth piece for Jalapao.
He's heading back, rope and all.
Tyson makes very fast work of
his knots.
Sandy now out on the course for
Jalapao.
Sierra now out on the course.
Both tribes are halfway there.
Four pieces left.
>> Go, Sandy!
Go, Sandy! Whoo!
Go, Sandy!
>> PROBST: Jalapao still with
a slight advantage over Timbira.
>> Go, Sandy!
>> PROBST: Sydney out on the
course for Jalapao.
Debra out on the course for
Timbira.
Three pieces left.
>> All right, Syd, kill this!
>> Good job, Debbie!
>> PROBST: Sydney really
struggling with her knots.
>> She's making me nauseous.
Sydney, come on.
>> PROBST: Timbira now in the
lead.
Brendan back out on the course
for Timbira.
Sydney sprinting back.
Joe back out on the course
again.
>> Come on, Joe-Joe!
Come on, Joe-Joe!
>> PROBST: Brendan through his
knots quickly.
>> All right, Joe!
>> PROBST: Joe unclips.
>> Go get them.
>> PROBST: Tyson heading out
for the final piece for Timbira.
>> Yeah, Joe. Good job.
>> PROBST: J.T. on the course
for final piece for Jalapao.
Tyson has the last puzzle piece
for Timbira.
>> Good job, Tyson!
>> PROBST: J.T. made up a lot of
time.
J.T. has the last piece for
Jalapao.
>> J.T.! Whoo!
>> PROBST: Timbira, start
working on your puzzle.
Jalapao, start working on your
puzzle.
>> Look out. Look out.
>> PROBST: There are two
elements to this puzzle.
You have to make sure each
piece is in the correct spot.
Then, you have to rotate it to
the correct side...
to find the winning phrase.
Second chance you guys have had
to work together on a word
puzzle.
>> Oh, okay, guys.
>> PROBST: Timbira froze the
last time we did this.
>> No, I think "win" or
"immunity" is wrong.
It's to confuse us.
It doesn't make any sense to
have a freakin' phrase that ends
with "win" or "immunity."
>> Right, you're right.
You're right.
>> PROBST: There are lots of
phrases that are almost right.
>> ...your tribe wins.
Your tribe wins...
>> PROBST: Only one that is
absolutely right.
>> Do we see "Timbira" anywhere?
>> "Escaped."
"Jalapao."
"Tribal."
"Council."
"Immunity."
>> Yes.
>> That's it!
>> No, it's not.
>> "Escape the vote."
Let's get it. Go back.
"Escape the vote."
>> This one, this one, this one.
>> Grab it.
>> This one right here.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Switch this one!
(cheering)
>> We need somebody.
>> PROBST: Timbira thinks they
have it.
"Escape the vote.
Timbira wins immunity."
Timbira does win immunity.
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Timbira,
congratulations.
>> Yes!
Yes!
>> PROBST: No Tribal Council
tonight.
Nobody else from your tribe
going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Enjoy the night off.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Tough Tribal tonight,
J.T.?
>> Very tough, Jeff.
We've become one group here,
one tribe.
Nobody wants to go home.
Nobody wants to vote anybody
else home, so it's going to be
real tough.
>> PROBST: Unfortunately,
somebody is going home.
And after tonight's vote, both
tribes will be even again.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> The challenge was something
that we took as our big
opportunity to gain numbers in
this game, and hold them for a
long time.
But right now, we're going to
go back to six on six.
So it was just, overall, very
frustrating.
>> We see all these words, but
it's just like there is no rhyme
or reason.
God, it was just so random.
>> I think it's the curse of
the beans.
>> I was not surprised that we
lost because we went on a
four-challenge winning streak,
so I definitely thought that it
was coming.
I just need to cool off.
I'm so dehydrated.
Sierra and I found the last
clue for the idol.
I know exactly where it is.
I'll talk to Stephen as soon as
I get a second, but right now,
we need to focus on Tribal
Council.
>> I mean, honestly, I'm kind
of glad, though.
Not someone, but...
Someone... her names rhymes
with "Andy."
(Sydney laughs)
>> Oh, Lord.
So what are we going to do
tonight, y'all?
>> What do y'all think?
>> Oh, God...
>> I don't know.
I know I don't want to go home.
>> I don't want to go home.
>> I'd also like not to go home.
>> Honestly, I'm going to put
this out there.
I think Sandy was stronger than
Sydney in the last two
competitions, honestly.
>> The problem if we eliminate
Sydney, Spencer and Joe both
are going to be...
>> They're going to turn on us.
>> Has she been really, like,
the catalyst in the challenges?
>> You know, she's strong.
She's not that strong in
challenges, you're right.
I mean, she's, you know, a nice
presence around camp.
She works hard.
She works hard around camp.
>> Yeah, yeah, we do.
>> I've got mixed emotions.
I don't feel bad and I don't
feel good, you know?
Taj is leaning towards Sydney,
and she said I'm doing better
in the challenges, actually,
than Sydney, but we'll see.
I think maybe J.T. and them are
telling me the truth and I'm
going to be here tomorrow.
>> It's up to y'all.
Just let me and know I'll do
whatever y'all want me to do.
>> I will.
The important thing is now is
figuring out am I going to send
Sandy home or am I going to
send Sydney home?
I have a big dilemma right now.
I'm not sure what I want to do.
>> I was excited to meet other
people who I would never get a
chance to meet.
And also just to see how I
would like, fare.
>> I like the sneakiness of it,
too, 'cause I'm not very sneaky
back home, you know?
So you get to be sneaky in a
new environment.
>> Oh, really?
>> So you're being sneaky?
That's interesting.
>> Yeah, I'm glad you told me
that.
>> That's good information.
>> All of y'all are sneaky, too,
so don't even start with me.
>> Sydney's good looks make a
positive first impression, but
that could be, you know, part
of her devious personality.
If there's a merge coming up,
we need strong members, but we
also need loyal members, so
getting rid of Sydney could
make a lot of sense.
>> As far I know, the vote's
going to be going on to Sandy K.
tonight.
I feel like I've tried to get
on the good sides of people,
so, hopefully, it's not me.
But then again, it's Survivor.
So, you know, everyone wants to
win.
So we'll see.
>> PROBST: Sandy, going back to
day one, you were out of this
game.
Here we are on day 12, you're
still sitting pretty.
Have you recovered from that
first impression?
>> I believe I did recover.
I fit in with this gang quite
well, given the fact that, uh,
you know, I'm the older woman.
So, yeah, it makes me feel good.
Believe me.
>> PROBST: J.T., how did Sandy
recover from such an awful
start?
>> Well, Sandy's kind of the
mother of the crowd.
She takes care of us and frees
us up to do the hard work.
>> PROBST: Sandy, do you spend
any time at all reflecting on
your age when you're spending
so much time with people that
are considerably younger and
relatively speaking,
a good-looking group of people?
>> Yes, the old age factor
plays a part in that, but, you
know, I bring them a lot of
laughs and so forth.
But I think people might use
their, maybe, a little bit of
their beauty or their body, you
know?
I've seen a little bit of
flirting going on as far as
Sydney is concerned, you know?
Maybe wearing the boxer shorts
of J.T., you know.
>> PROBST: J.T., is she wearing
your boxers?
>> Yeah, Jeff, she's wearing my
boxers.
>> It's hot out there.
I don't have shorts.
I'm wearing jeans.
>> PROBST: Nobody asked you to
defend.
>> I know, that's all I'm
saying though.
>> PROBST: Joe, do you see that
going on?
>> Yeah.
Yeah, I see flirting going on.
>> PROBST: Stephen, fair part
of the game?
If you're a young, beautiful
woman, why not try to use it
to influence the guys?
>> First of all, I should say
that the big flirting
relationship has not been
mentioned yet, which is between
Sydney and Joe.
They flirt maybe a little more
than J.T. and Sydney flirt.
>> PROBST: Sydney, you were
nodding your head and smiling.
>> Yeah, I mean, I have a
flirtatious personality.
I flirt with women.
I definitely flirt with Joe.
He's a great guy.
I get along with him really
well.
It's just inevitable for me,
I think.
>> PROBST: Taj, how's that sit
with you?
>> First of all, let's just say
Sydney is gorgeous.
So men are definitely going to
be attracted to her,
regardless.
They can't help themselves.
So if there's an alliance, it
would be with her and not me
because she probably what they
want to align with anyway.
And that's okay because I'll
make my way through the game
regardless.
>> PROBST: Hold on.
"That's okay"?
>> It's okay with me, oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: I don't buy that for
a second.
>> I have to accept the fact
that they are attracted to her.
They're not attracted to me.
That's okay with me.
I'll be all right with or
without their attraction.
>> PROBST: Sydney, does this
happen to you a lot?
Conversations end up revolving
around your looks?
>> Yeah, it happens a lot.
My profession is a model, you
know?
So people stereotype me as the
blonde girl who doesn't have a
lot to stay and sits there and
be pretty.
But, that doesn't mean, like...
I don't know.
It's hard to explain.
>> PROBST: Stephen, could that
work against Sydney?
>> Definitely.
I mean, someone could think,
"Oh, she's just a flirt; she's
nothing," and just undervalue
her throughout the game.
>> PROBST: Sandy, how will this
tribe be different tomorrow?
>> I think there might be a
person or two upset, depending
on the outcome.
I imagine there'll be a couple
of real upsets.
So tomorrow will tell the story.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Joe, you're up.
>> It's just your time to go.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sandy.
Sydney.
One vote Sandy; one vote Sydney.
Joe.
One vote Sandy;
one vote Sydney;
one vote Joe.
Sandy.
That's two votes Sandy;
one vote Sydney; one vote Joe.
Sandy.
>> Oh, boy.
>> PROBST: That's three votes
Sandy; one vote Sydney;
one vote Joe.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Tocantins: Sandy.
That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Sandy, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, after tonight's vote,
both tribes are even: six-six.
Brand-new game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS PARAMOUNT
NETWORK TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Once we make it to the
merge, it's smooth sailing.
>> PROBST: The secret
cross-Tribal alliance
might not be so secret.
>> And I'm sick of this game.
>> PROBST: And Taj acts out.
>> Everybody can kiss my ass.
>> Moves like that will get you
voted off.
>> I'm hot today.
>> I was slung out, you know,
right off the bat, the first
day without anybody knowing me
or anything.
And then I kind of got in with
them.
I was like the mother, uh,
mother hen over all these little
ducks.
And I stayed around a lot
longer than I thought I was
going to.
And, uh, I didn't quit.
So I'm real proud of myself.