>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: After the merge...
>> We're now one tribe!
>> PROBST: The old Galu tribe
was up eight to four.
>> Right now, the Galu tribe is
tight.
We confirmed, that you know
what? Let's stick together.
>> PROBST: And they anticipated
that the rest of the old Foa Foa
would go out quickly and easily.
>> What you need to know
you know.
>> PROBST: But the Foa Foa four
resolved not to go out gently.
>> We all hoped to put a big
dent in that arrogance and
patronizing attitude they have
towards us.
>> PROBST: First they convinced
the old Galu to vote out one of
their own.
>> I don't trust Erik.
>> PROBST: When Erik left,
Galu's numbers dropped down to
seven.
The tribe has spoken.
At the next Tribal Council, the
old Galu was set to take out
Russell.
But he shocked them by playing
the hidden immunity idol.
>> Keep hope alive.
>> PROBST: So Kelly went home,
leaving Galu with only six
members.
Or so it would seem.
But the old Galu doesn't know
that one of their own, Shambo,
is conspiring with Russell to
get rid of Laura.
>> Shambo hates Laura.
She hates her.
>> Laura needs to go.
She's the bane of my existence.
>> PROBST: Well, since the
merge, there have been two
Tribal Councils, two
blind sides, two hidden immunity
idols played, and once again,
the Foa Foa foursome have
survived the vote.
One more thing, the hidden
immunity idol goes back into
the game.
>> My work is done.
It's like a painting, like a
Picasso, you know?
He's a great artist.
This is my artwork.
This might be one of my best
pieces of work I've ever done.
There's going to be a pretty
expensive sale.
They'll write me a check for
$1 million for this work, so I
can take that...
Take that to the bank.
>> If you guys tell Galu I said
this-- "good move!"
>> Let me tell you something,
that was almost as great as my
kids being born.
(laughter)
>> Dude.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah, wow.
>> I cannot believe that little
snake...
>> Part of the game.
>> Yep.
>> Yes, it is.
>> We've still got the numbers.
>> It was quite the shock at
Tribal Council tonight when
Russell pulled out that second
hidden immunity idol.
We know that he's sneaky and
that he just, like, lurks
around camp and he's always
snooping around.
We should have known better.
We really should have known
better.
>> Oh, you're in trouble.
>> (laughing)
>> Oh, my God,
the look on her face when you
played that immunity idol.
Do you know what she said when
they said, "Kelly, bring me
your torch."
She goes, "He has ruined
everything."
And it was all I could do to
keep a straight face.
>> I ruined everything?
What does she think I'm here
for her, for to bake her
cookies and cakes?
(laughter)
>> Nobody out of the 11
people had a clue what the hell
was going on with the exception
of me and Russ, and when he got
up and played that immunity
idol, the look on Laura's face--
she was just pissed.
It was awesome.
And I was thinking I got to
find that immunity idol, give
it to Russ again.
♪ ♪
>> It's a new beginning.
Jeff said the immunity idol is
back in the game, and I'll be
here looking for it, and I will
find it.
It will be the third one.
It's like, they're like magnets
to me.
I'm just drawn to them.
>> Okay.
Work.
>> Laura is the head viper.
She is the viper queen of Galu.
She is the snake of the tribe.
She is the evil demon.
She's a beast.
Laura has been the first one to
go in my mind since day one.
>> I want to relax a bit this
morning.
I want to swing by the wall,
Sham, and just...
>> Yeah.
I got four Foa Foa.
I got me.
We're on an even playing field
right now.
I have to have John.
He's my number six.
Hold on a second.
Come here.
>> What's up?
>> Here's the thing-- you know,
it's all well and fine that
everybody wants to espouse
purple power.
There is no purple.
It takes balls to jump into
this arena.
And how far do you want to
extend your life?
The next immunity challenge,
just like the last two, Laura's
won, and both times, Laura was
supposed to go for the majority
of the tribe.
So I want to know that if she
doesn't win it, will you be the
sixth vote to put her out?
>> I don't have an answer to
that question right now.
I don't.
I believe I am the only one
from Galu that knows that
Shambo has flipped.
Now the question is what are
you going to do with it?
>> Will you betray my
confidence that I asked you
that question?
>> I won't-- I won't-- I will
look you straight in the eyes
and I will not tell anyone
that you asked me that question.
Things are on the table with
Shambo.
She thinks she's in good with
me, and she is.
>> Okay. Thanks, Johnny.
>> But, you know what?
I've got do what's right for me.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's challenge, you will
divide into two teams of five.
One person from each team will
lie facedown in a cradle
suspended in the air.
Attached to that cradle are
four ropes.
The other four people will pull
on the ropes to maneuver the
person in the cradle as they
gather 15 flags one at a time
in order and place them in
their appropriate spot.
First team to get all 15 wins
reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: The winning team
will board a plane and fly to
the neighboring island of
Savai'i.
You'll land at a beautiful
waterfall and have a nice
picnic lunch.
>> During the reward, I'm
thinking that they're going to
be giving out a clue for the
next hidden immunity idol.
Man, if I can find this clue,
that-that's it.
It's over.
>> PROBST: In addition, you
will take with you the Palm Pre
by Sprint.
Now, you'll have something that
fits in the palm of your hand,
is easy to use, and will allow
you to take some great
photographs, make some fun
memories of a truly
once-in-a-lifetime experience.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: All right.
We'll draw for teams and get
started.
All right, we have our two
teams.
Yellow-- Shambo, Jaison,
Monica, and Mick with John in
the cradle.
For purple, we have Dave Ball,
Brett, Laura and Russell, with
Natalie in the cradle.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go.
You have to use the four ropes
to maneuver your person to get
their flags.
Natalie has the first flag for
purple.
She's got to get it in the slot.
John has the first flag for
yellow.
John drops the flag.
There's a learning curve.
>> You got it, you got it, stick
it in.
>> PROBST: Natalie has the first
flag for purple.
>> Take your time.
Hold on, watch the ropes.
>> PROBST: Yellow can't get the
gri--
There it is.
John has the flag again.
>> Turn me, turn me, turn me.
>> PROBST: Natalie has the
second flag for purple.
>> You guys, sit on your butts.
>> Got it.
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: John gets the
first flag.
Purple doing very well.
>> That's a girl.
>> PROBST: John has the second
flag for yellow.
Natalie has the third flag for
purple.
>> Sit on your butts!
Sit on your butts.
>> PROBST: Jaison, Shambo, Mick
and Monica now getting it
together.
>> That's a girl.
Force to the right.
>> PROBST: Purple with their
third flag.
Yellow with two flags.
>> Little closer.
>> PROBST: Natalie reaching for
number four, she has it.
>> Got it, go, come on!
>> PROBST: Purple has their
fourth flag.
Yellow has their third flag.
Natalie with the fifth flag for
purple.
Yellow hanging-- nope, nope,
nope.
Yellow knocked out number 9.
You got to get it back in its
slot now.
>> That's a girl.
You're doing great.
You're there.
>> PROBST: That is really going
to cost them some time.
>> Come on, get it down!
>> PROBST: You almost got it.
John has it.
He's got to get it back in its
slot now before he can go on.
You're good.
Purple has their seventh flag.
>> Go, keep your ropes up.
Keep your ropes up.
Come on! Let's go!
John quickly gets the fifth
flag for yellow.
>> That's a girl!
>> There you go.
Let's go, let's go!
>> PROBST: Natalie now with the
eighth flag for purple.
John has the sixth flag for
yellow.
>> Stay in there!
>> PROBST: Natalie hanging on
with her legs.
You got this, girl.
>> Good job!
>> Grab it!
>> PROBST: John has seven.
They're still in it.
>> Good job, Nat!
>> PROBST: Natalie has the
ninth flag for purple.
>> That's the stuff!
>> PROBST: Yellow have seven.
>> Come on.
>> Eight's over here!
>> Down.
>> PROBST: Natalie hanging out
of that cradle.
>> Get closer, pull down.
>> PROBST: Using all of
her body.
She's got the tenth flag.
>> Right there, right there.
>> Let's go.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Yellow trying to make
up some time.
>> Right there!
>> PROBST: Natalie has the tenth
flag for purple.
Five flags left.
Natalie has the 11th flag.
Yellow has their eighth flag.
Natalie with the 12th flag for
purple looking for 13.
>> You got this, girl!
>> Take me home!
>> I got you, John, go!
>> PROBST: John places number
nine.
Natalie has 14.
Purple has one flag left.
>> Hang on, baby!
Hang on, baby!
>> Hold on, Natalie!
>> PROBST: Natalie, don't fall
out.
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> Hang on, Natalie.
Last one.
>> We got this, we got this!
Yeah!
>> PROBST: That's it!
Purple has the 15th
and final flag.
Got to get it in the slot.
>> Keep your ropes up.
>> Go, go, go!
>> Slowly, don't let her fall.
>> PROBST: For a nice reward.
>> Come on!
You know what it's for!
>> Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
>> PROBST: Purple wins reward!
Russell, Brett, Dave Ball,
Laura and Natalie going
on reward.
>> Good girl. Come on.
>> Come on, Nat.
>> You were awesome!
>> That was great!
>> PROBST: Purple,
congratulations.
You're gonna enjoy a
wonderful afternoon.
In addition, Palm Pre by Sprint.
Make some memories.
Take some photos.
Enjoy it.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: John, Monica,
Jaison, Shambo, Mick, got
nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> If I can find this clue for
the next hidden immunity idol,
then I can't see how it's not
gonna be possible for me to
do what I want to do and take
out Laura.
>> We won a reward today:
Natalie, me,
Laura, Brett, and Dave.
Now, we get to fly to another
island, eat and take pictures
with a Sprint phone, which is
wonderful.
I need to eat, bad.
>> It's like a little
Gilligan's island or something,
huh?
>> Oh, my word, it's so cool.
>> I think that's the island
we're going to.
>> Really?
>> Who's gonna eat?
>> Uh!
>> I'm gonna eat.
>> Oh, my gosh!
It's hot dogs!
That I love! Oh!
>> Give me a plate.
>> I want some of that good
old pie.
>> I've had dreams about you,
baby.
>> Oh, my goodness, finally,
day 26, I get to go on a reward
and I needed the food.
I literally was, like,
wasting away.
>> Oh, my God! Try that pie.
>> It felt just like home.
It was really, really nice.
I just felt really thankful to
have gotten to go.
>> Thank you for allowing me
and Russell to come on our
first reward.
>> Congratulations.
>> I'm glad you guys could
take part.
>> You guys. One, two, three.
>> Seems like you guys are
pretty tight.
I know we're tight.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I know where the votes are
right now.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And...
you know, if we, if we
essentially feel like if we get
one more on our side, we're
willing to offer them a very,
very good deal.
>> I don't know.
Just don't know.
You know what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> It's risky.
>> We just need to make a
decision, go to challenge, and
go to Tribal Council.
>> But, I mean, we need
another-- we need one more vote.
>> No, we don't.
>> Yeah, we do.
>> You're number six.
>> It's still gonna be 5-5.
>> We have five besides you.
>> Five besides you.
>> You are number six.
>> You're six.
>> Which is why we asked.
We need six.
>> How sure are you?
>> 115%.
>> How do you know they're not
just saying it to you?
>> We know.
'Cause let's put it this way--
this person knew about the last
Tribal Council.
>> Right.
And he or she actually
encouraged things to make that
whole thing happen.
>> I'm thinking that one of the
other people that they're
talking about is Shambo.
Shambo could be the fifth vote
for the Foa Foas.
You can't tell me who that is?
>> No, we won't.
>> I want John out.
>> We can absolutely do that.
>> Great.
>> What a great day, guys.
>> This is phenomenal.
Best reward so far, Dave?
>> Best reward so far.
>> Looking through the photos,
I seen a note that's telling us
"Go to your memo board," and
you'll get the clue.
First thing that pops in my
head-- hidden immunity idol.
That would be my third one.
>> "This Palm in your hand
"holds much information which
"you better heed or it will be
"your own loss.
"The immunity idol is no
"rolling stone.
"A rolling stone gathers
no moss."
>> A rolling stone gathers what?
>> "No moss."
>> I'm gonna look all over
the place.
I'll find it, for sure.
I'll find it.
>> "Go to videos to watch an
"additional clue to the hidden
immunity idol."
Okay, I'll watch it and then
pass it on.
"Additional hint."
>> The immunity idol is under a
stinking rock.
>> Eight seconds.
That's it.
>> I ain't got to see it again.
As soon as I go back to camp,
I'm gonna start looking for
it 'cause I need the immunity
idol for myself.
>> Shambo!
>> Hi, you guys!
Hello! I missed you!
It's about that big.
It's not a round rock.
It's square.
It has moss on it.
>> Can you show us there?
>> They're moving.
>> No.
>> Those guys are already
moving.
>> We totally underestimated
Russell's capability of finding
the idol.
What we need to do is keep that
hidden immunity idol out of
Russell's hands.
>> It's time to hunt.
>> I guess so.
>> The party's on.
>> There you go.
>> You finding for the same
thing I'm looking for, Jaison?
>> I don't know.
What are you looking for?
>> You're the one that's
lifting up rocks.
>> Here's a green.
>> No, it's too new.
I know that it has to be where
that wall is in camp.
They have a rock in a little
hole, square hole.
Looks like the rock in the
picture to me.
Dave's following me around,
turning over rocks.
I get nervous at first 'cause
I think I see the rock and then
he turns it over and
nothing's there.
So I'm figuring if all of
this...
You think you can run with me?
>> We're just gonna put y'all...
Oh, man!
>> Slow down, Russ!
>> All right. Come on, Dave.
>> Slow down, man, slow down!
All right.
Come on, Dave.
>> I came back
to the same location.
I'm looking at the wall.
Look down there.
There it is.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
This is getting way too easy.
I'm enjoying it.
I'm just running around.
I'm having more fun now than
I've ever had, and my butt's
probably in the sling more than
ever, but not if they think I
have an idol.
I'm gonna be a-okay.
♪ ♪
I mean...
I don't trust Shambo or John.
And Shambo hates you.
And she's pissed, Laura.
We have to be careful.
They might come after you.
>> They'll come after me first.
I think the Foa Foa people are
coming after me.
I've had a target on my head
from them from day one.
Sham just completely
despises me.
I need to be on the top of my
game, and I have to win this
challenge.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to
today's immunity challenge?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Laura, give it up.
Once again, immunity back up
for grabs.
Today's challenge happens in
two parts:
first part, you'll have three
tiles of the same color
arranged close together.
Your goal? Throw one rock and
attempt to break as many of
these tiles as you can.
For every tile you break, you
earn a spear, which you will
use in the second part of the
challenge when you will shoot
your spears at a target.
Person who lands their spear
closest to the target wins
immunity, guaranteed a one-in-
nine shot at a million dollars.
Losers, Tribal Council.
Somebody will be voted out.
Make sense?
>> Yeah.
Makes sense.
>> PROBST: We draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, everybody grab
one rock.
If you want a shot at immunity,
you've got to break a tile.
These tiles are arranged
close together.
That means you could break
multiple tiles.
It also means somebody could
break one of yours.
But you've only got one throw.
Here we go.
Ready?
Aim...
and throw.
>> Son of a gun!
>> PROBST: Shambo just misses.
Russell goes low.
Jaison's on the board with
one spear.
>> Damn.
>> PROBST: Fincher just misses.
Monica can't get it there.
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Dave Ball knocks out
one of Monica's tiles.
Monica now has a spear.
>> Enjoy, money.
>> Thanks, honey.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Natalie a little
short.
>> Nice.
>> Oh, bummer!
>> PROBST: Mick connects with
one of his tiles.
>> Brett breaks two tiles with
one toss.
>> PROBST: Laura, the only
person left to throw.
You want a shot at immunity,
this is it.
You have to break a tile.
That's it.
>> (laughing)
>> PROBST: No shot at immunity
for Laura, Russell, Shambo,
John, Natalie, and Dave Ball.
All right, moving on to the
second part of the challenge.
Brett has two spears.
Jaison, Mick, and Monica have
one.
Let's go.
Brett, you're up.
>> Sounds good.
>> Go, Brett.
>> Go, B.
>> PROBST: Brett taking aim of
his first shot.
>> Come on, baby.
(applause)
>> Good job, Brett!
>> PROBST: Brett is on the
board.
>> Good job, Brett!
>> PROBST: Brett has the mark
to beat.
Jaison, you're up.
To have a shot at immunity,
Jaison has to get inside the
mark set by Brett, currently in
that second ring.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Jaison misses the
target completely.
Jaison, no shot at immunity.
Monica.
Monica here thanks to Dave Ball
who broke one of Monica's tiles.
Monica fires.
Hits the target but too low.
Monica, no shot at immunity.
>> Good shot.
>> Good job.
>> Good try, Monica.
>> PROBST: Mick.
One spear.
That's all it takes, one shot
could win it.
Mick with a great shot.
Puts his spear inside of
Brett's.
Mick is the new mark to beat.
It comes down to this.
Brett, one spear left.
You know what you have to do.
Take your shot.
>> Take your time, babe.
>> PROBST: Brett hits too low.
Mick wins individual immunity.
(applause)
>> Good job, Mick.
>> PROBST: Mick, come on over.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Mick safe at
tonight's Tribal Council.
For one of you, that will be as
far as it goes.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you tonight at
Tribal Council.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> I believe it is the destiny
of Laura to go home.
Today is the day of reckoning.
Medusa's head will be lopped
off.
>> Does anybody want any of this
coconut?
>> Are you going to open that
thing up?
>> I'm going to give it
a sh...
>> Isn't that the cotton candy
ones?
>> You got a feeling?
>> I got a feeling.
>> The plan is and always was
for the last nine days is get
rid of Laura.
She keeps winning immunity.
She finally loses, we got to
get rid of her.
I was happy about that.
Because I knew at least, okay,
at least, we have a tie.
And now, we have a fighting
chance because it's five to five
because Shambo is voting Laura.
There's no if, ands, and buts
about that.
She's voting Laura.
>> I'm voting for Laura
tonight, and I don't care who
else is doing what.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I really don't.
But...
>> You're not going to
fluctuate or change at all?
>> There's no way in God's
green Earth.
Had she not won immunity the
last two times, that's whose
name I would have written down.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> She's too strong and she's
too manipulative.
>> Okay.
>> There is no more Galu.
>> What's up?
>> We were going to ask,
because we were talking about
some stuff, and I said we need
to go talk to John.
Because he's the number
cruncher.
>> What's up?
>> Keep it simple, just get rid
of the Foa Foa.
Wait until the very last minute
so they don't know who it is.
We vote Russell.
If he has the idol, he plays
it, it flushes out--
>> Incorrect.
>> Okay.
>> The answer is Natalie.
>> And the reason is she's the
least likely to have the idol
because she didn't look for it.
The vote is Natalie, times five.
>> Perfect.
>> Find a problem with that.
Is that wrong?
>> Five guys?
Okay, okay.
>> I know you'd rather not have
Natalie.
No, no, no, I like that.
>> I'll burn her right now, I
do not care, bro.
>> It's continually impressive
and bordering on annoying how
pathetic the analytical skills
of the Galu tribe are.
"Let's telegraph a move to
Russell."
You're an idiot.
"Let's sit back and let's piss
off Shambo."
You're an idiot.
"Let's sit back and vote off
Erik over a 30-second decision."
You're an idiot.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Laura's going home.
>> No, no.
>> Yes, because Shambo will
vote for Laura.
>> I know, but it's a 5-5 tie.
5-5 tie.
It may be true--
>> Right.
>> But you're saying it as if it
is a certainty, game over.
That is not the case.
>> They're on the fence.
Some people are saying John.
>> That's great.
>> So if we say John, so keep
it with John?
>> So that means, like, we need
to go talk to Mick or something.
>> Oh, that's brilliant.
I'll say John, and then they
think they have two Galu saying
John.
>> Let's just think about it.
>> But it's an option.
It's a good option.
>> It is a good option.
Just don't get excited.
John is flighty.
So we don't want to do anything
premature.
We want to give it some more
thought.
>> Absolutely.
>> Because he gets nervous.
>> That's fine.
>> All right, cool.
>> This is a big move, you guys.
>> We'll make it happen.
It'll be beautiful.
>> Just be confident.
>> Yeah, be confident.
Confident.
>> Laura's my strongest ally
here, and I do not want to
throw her under the bus, so the
plan is for me to tell Foa Foa
that I am voting for John.
In reality, I would be voting
Natalie with my tribe.
So hopefully all goes to plan
and it'll be four Foa Foa
members voting John, five Galu
members voting Natalie, and
then the one, Shambo, voting
Laura.
Listen I think if we get rid of
John now.
>> Look I want to--
>> Listen, listen, if we do
it now, we still have Shambo
against Laura and then we have
even more numbers.
>> Look, look, look, look,
Shambo is not doing no other
vote but Laura tonight.
It's going to end up by being a
tie you don't go Laura.
And I was with that from the
beginning.
>> I'm not ready to write
Laura's name.
If I'm switching, this is a
huge move for me, Russell.
If I'm switching, I'm not going
to vote out, like...
I'm going to vote out someone I
want to vote out.
Do you see that?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> John's smart.
>> Yeah, I know.
I want to get rid of John.
We need to get him out now.
This is a huge move for me.
And the thing is, is that I
would rather take out John than
Laura.
>> Okay, all right.
>> Just because, I mean, in the
end, I need to have some sort
of security blanket, and I
don't trust John.
Do you see what I'm saying?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> I don't know how much Foa
Foa can trust Monica.
She seems legit, or Laura has
put, you know, a little snake
in the grass to get
information, which is almost as
likely.
>> She makes me a little
nervous, but I like to think
she's on our side.
>> You know what?
I want to get the okay from
y'all, but I think the only way
this is going to work is to let
John know.
>> Let John know what?
>> Let him know that they're
after him.
That's the only way this is
going to work, dude.
>> He doesn't trust us.
>> It's going to be a tie.
It's going to be a tie.
>> What's the plan?
Where's Shambo at today?
>> What's the response?
>> It's like, trying to get
them to vote for you, Shambo's
voting for Laura, four would
vote for you.
And none of us would go for
another one.
>> Yeah, well, I haven't said
anything.
Shambo-- honestly, Shambo's
going to vote for Laura no
matter what.
We've got to think of another
option to deter their votes.
>> Well, I can come up with
something, but the answer is to
not get four votes against me.
The most recent development
today is that the new best way
to save Laura is to throw four
Foa Foa votes behind John.
Uh, no.
It doesn't sound like a good
plan when you're John.
>> We're just thinking through
ideas, how can we shake up the
Foas?
>> All right, you guys are
betting my life that Shambo
votes for Laura.
We are betting nothing.
>> I would.
>> Well, let's bet yours and
not mine, then.
Because I wouldn't.
>> Everyone's got your back.
>> I'm not risking my life to
save Laura's.
Sorry, Laura, not in the cards.
Laura picked a fight with
somebody that I think is about
to knock her out.
And I'm not going to step in
the way of the punch.
>> I was born at night but not
last night. Right?
>> What have you heard?
>> I believe that we're trying
to be swindled into telling us
to put your name down,
everybody is.
I don't believe that.
We're putting Laura's name
down, and we're going to go to
the tie.
>> If there is a tie tonight,
the rules of Survivor state
there is a re-vote.
If there is a tie again, the
remaining members now choose
rocks.
One of these rocks will be of
different color, and that
person will go home.
>> If it goes to the tie,
that's when it has to happen,
the switch.
>> If I vote for Laura tonight,
after the tie, I wake up on
this beach tomorrow.
>> I done talked to everybody.
Everybody's on the same page.
We said whoever does the
switch, that's who we know is
on board.
If they don't do the switch, we
pick a rock.
>> And-and what's the next vote?
>> The next vote?
>> If I'm going to give you
Galu before you give me a Foa
Foa, the next one needs to be
Foa Foa.
>> Okay.
>> Deal?
>> That's a deal.
>> But Russell is a player.
This guy is full of B.S.
And it's clear the guy will do
anything to progress in this
game.
My first instinct is the best
situation that I can position
myself in would be to vote with
Galu, have a 5-5 tie, vote with
Galu again, have another 5-5
tie, and just pray to God that
one of the Foa Foa members go.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm going to
do yet.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Erik and Kelly voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
John, are you surprised, two
Tribal Councils, two Galu
sitting over there?
>> Absolutely.
Both of the two votes so far
were surprises to me.
It's all a surprise.
>> PROBST: Jaison, is it easier
in some sense at this point to
be the minority because with
four, you don't have as many
many options?
You have to stick together.
>> Sure, you could make
that argument.
And because we're the minority,
if people want to use the
votes, they can depend on our
trustworthiness to go further.
>> PROBST: John, what is
appealing about the Foa Foa
foursome?
>> They've already said it.
You can use four votes.
It's plain and simple.
>> Yeah, we've said it, but
we still trying to find
somebody.
>> We're trying to figure out,
like, at what point somebody
says, "Oh, hey.
This is an individual game,"
and take advantage of our votes,
and start playing their
own game.
>> PROBST: Shambo, is Galu one
tight unit still?
>> Negative.
Absolutely not.
The day that everybody decided
to vote Erik off, Galu was
broken to me.
That's my humble opinion.
>> PROBST: Laura, you're still
staring at Shambo.
>> I don't know who she's
talking about because the Galu
that I know, that I've been in,
I feel is tight.
>> PROBST: A group can't be
tight if one of the members
isn't.
>> I guess it depends on how
big of a group you're
considering.
>> PROBST: Well, here's what I
would consider.
If Shambo's on the fence, their
four becomes five, your six
becomes five-- we got a
really interesting night
in store.
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: Are you okay with it
potentially coming down to a
tie knowing that, if we revote
and you're still tied,
everybody over here will draw
rocks, and the people who are
tied will be safe?
>> I'm absolutely not okay with
taking a chance.
But I'm not the only one in
control of this game.
I have these other people
sitting next to me that have
decisions to make as well.
>> PROBST: Dave, are you okay
with this going to a tie?
>> If I need to go to the
stones, then I'll go.
>> PROBST: After 27 days, you
would draw a stone at chance
and you're prepared to do that?
>> You got to be willing to
make big moves in this game in
order to win.
I'd say there's nothing bigger
than lady luck.
>> PROBST: I always love it
when it gets to the vote, but
tonight I am especially curious
how it's gonna go.
Mick, you have individual
immunity.
I can't imagine you're giving
it up tonight.
>> Nope.
>> PROBST: Cannot vote for Mick.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Brett, you're up.
>> (whispering): Laura, you are
a viper, as in poison.
I pray to God you go tonight.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally
the votes.
>> If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Laura.
Natalie.
One vote Laura,
one vote Natalie.
Laura.
Two votes Laura.
Natalie. Two votes Natalie.
Laura.
That's three votes Laura,
twp votes Natalie.
Natalie.
We're tied, three votes Laura,
three votes Natalie.
That's four votes Laura,
Natalie.
Four votes Natalie,
four votes Laura.
Laura.
That's five votes Laura,
four votes Natalie.
One vote left.
Natalie.
We have a tie.
Here's how the tie's
gonna work:
Laura and Natalie, you will
not vote.
Everybody else will vote.
You can only vote for Laura
or Natalie.
Brett, you're up first.
Come grab the urn.
>> I'm ready to roll the dice.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: I'll go tally
the votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Laura.
Natalie.
One vote Laura,
one vote Natalie.
Two votes Laura,
Tied again.
two votes Natalie.
Laura.
That's three votes Laura,
two votes Natalie.
Natalie.
We're tied, three votes Laura,
three votes Natalie,
two votes left.
Laura.
That's four votes Laura,
three votes Natalie.
One vote left.
Ninth person voted out and the
third member of our jury, Laura.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Laura, the tribe
has spoken.
Well, since the merge, there
have been three very surprising
Tribal Councils.
At this point, I don't know if
it's Galu, Foa Foa or Aiga.
And I'm guessing you guys
don't either.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time
on Survivor:
>> It's time for me
for me to create chaos.
(chicken clucking)
>> Shambo is the one leading
the charge.
>> Let's just pull the trigger.
>> I agree.
>> He's a cancer.
We have to dump him now.
>> Sometimes you just have to
say, "Screw it.
I'm gonna follow."
>> So Mick's on aboard with
the plan.
>> Yeah, we're all, we're all
with you, Sham.
>> I believe that I'm sitting
here tonight for a couple of
reasons: one, because Shambo
has always had it out for me,
and, two, I think that I was a
physical threat.
Clearly, it wasn't a good idea
going into the first two
individual immunity challenges
and winning them back to back.
I'm disappointed, but I hope
that Galu sticks together and
someone from the purple ends up
winning the million dollars.
So, good luck, guys.