>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: these 20 castaways
were marooned on the tiny
island nation of Samoa.
You guys have already been
divided into two tribes.
Wearing purple, you are Galu;
wearing yellow, you're Foa Foa.
At their camp, Galu had a
communications breakdown.
>> We have strong male
personalities that aren't
really hearing one another.
>> PROBST: but Galu's problems
were minor compared to Foa
Foa's.
The yellow tribe's biggest
problem is spelled
R-U-S-S-E-L-L.
Russell's plan is to perpetrate
every dirty trick in the book,
in order to win.
>> They can be my little
puppets.
When I'm finished with them,
just throw them in the trash.
>> PROBST: On their first
night, he sabotaged his own camp
just to make life miserable for
the others.
>> I think if I can control how
they feel, I can control how
they think.
>> PROBST: He made a series
secret alliances.
>> I got an alliance with the
dumb short-haired blonde, and an
even dumber long-haired blonde.
And the dark-haired girl.
I like to call it my dumb-ass
girl alliance.
>> PROBST: He constantly lied.
>> I lived in New Orleans.
The storm was a category 5.
When it hit, I tried to get out
of the house and I realized I
wasn't going to make it.
I never lived in New Orleans.
It's crazy how you can break
their hearts by telling them a
lie.
>> PROBST: after Foa Foa lost
the immunity challenge, Russell
needed a fall guy, so when
Marisa became suspicious of
him...
>> I'm starting to feel like
he's pretty slimy.
>> PROBST: He found his
sacrificial lamb.
>> What is that going to make
me think?
That makes me think I gotta get
rid of her.
>> Vote Marisa.
>> We're voting off Marisa.
>> PROBST: But not everybody was
on board with his scheme.
>> Marisa.
>> No.
>> She's going first.
If you stay with me, then
you're going to be fine for a
long time.
>> PROBST: Unfortunately for
Russell, Betsy's a cop and she
didn't believe a word he said.
>> As a police officer, I
usually can get a pretty good
read on somebody.
And I don't trust Russell.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Betsy went against Russell
and targeted Ashley as the
weakest player.
>> I think Ashley's the weakest.
>> PROBST: But Russell's sway
over the others was too strong.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa, Marisa.
Marisa was out, leaving Officer
Betsy to return to camp to
figure out where Russell will
strike next.
19 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Tribal Council was-- I
liked it.
I had fun because Marisa's gone
for no other reason but me, and
that's a fact.
If you play with fire, you're
going to get burned, and she
got burned.
I'm excited that Marisa is gone.
You know, I don't have to worry
about it no more.
I don't have to worry about her
strong mind.
I know that she's a strong
woman.
(screeching)
You can't have that out here.
I can't have it.
>> You see, the thing is, I...
I was telling you...
I didn't do anything for you
not to trust me, nothing.
You was going by appearance
only, I guess.
Or how I was trying to play the
game so fast.
Which I understand.
But I-I mean it, and I even told
the people I was with that I
want to keep you around as long
as I possibly can.
I think you made a huge
mistake, and you'll see that
later on.
>> Okay.
>> Because I was...
>> All right, as long as we
agree that we don't trust each
other, but we still can talk.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> I just don't... You didn't...
Why didn't you trust me from
the beginning?
You're not a threat to me.
It would be a perfect thing for
me to do.
But, anyway...
>> Okay.
>> It is what it is.
(laughs)
I feel fine that I
voted for Ashley last night.
I have no regrets.
But I think Russ felt very
threatened by Marisa.
He didn't like her.
She spoke her mind, but I'm not
afraid to stand up to him
at all.
He knows where I'm coming from.
He knows that I have no faith
in him, and I used to.
But not after getting to know
him.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Look at all the rashes.
They ate me up.
See, you even still look nice.
What's wrong with me?
Why do I look this bad?
>> Because you're funky, baby.
>> Oh, whatever.
Funky is the word.
Oh, my God.
I'm never taking my kids
camping.
This is crap.
I don't know who invented,
like, loving the outdoors.
Like, who can really love the
outdoors when you can be
indoors, 'cause this right here?
This is not for me.
>> Her back's all wet, poor
girl.
>> And then see, look at how I
have to walk, like a stick up
my butt.
Last night was horrible.
Lord have, mercy, God, I didn't
know it was going to be
this hard.
I was shaking, I was cold, I
was nauseated.
I don't know what was happening.
All I know is it was not good.
Look at that bed.
That bed is pitiful.
I've been told so many times,
"Oh, if you can make it in
Detroit, you can make it
anywhere."
What, the 'hood?
The 'hood is not the woods.
Ugh!
>> Yeah! I got a lizard!
Look, I got him right on the
dome, too, man.
>> Oh, what's up.
>> Stick a stick down his face
and roast him up.
>> All right, I just want to
make sure everything is good.
Last night was a little too
chaotic for me.
And I was a little shocked by
how aggressive you guys were
with Marisa last night.
I didn't know that either
hatred ran that deep, or that
you and Ben were that close.
>> Oh, that's not it.
It ain't nothing to do with
hatred.
It's just she was...
I thought she would be a real
powerful player.
Me and Ben was talking
about that.
I think, man, I trust you way
more than Ben.
>> Do you?
>> I think Jaison is somebody
perfect to bring with you,
because he's so calm and
collected.
He's an honest guy.
He's playing the game, playing
the challenges hard.
He's quiet, but he's likable.
You can't do this alone.
You gotta have somebody.
So if Jaison is the person that
I can trust, then this is going
to be real good.
Another thing, man, I think
there's an immunity idol in
our camp.
You gotta keep that a secret.
You know, and I should keep it
a secret, but the reason I'm
telling you is 'cause I trust
you, 'cause I'm going to start
looking for it.
'Cause if we can find that,
dude, without even any clues...
>> Yeah.
>> That would be wonderful.
>> Russell really wants to find
this hidden immunity idol.
We don't even know if there is
an immunity idol that's hidden
or going to come into existence
or whatever.
So, he's kind of, I guess,
trying to launch a preemptive
strike on trying to figure out
where that thing would be.
>> Don't put anything green in
this fire.
>> if I can find that idol,
then that would be genius.
In the history of Survivor,
how many people found the idol
without a clue?
Zero.
>> I think you'll like this,
Mick.
>> Yeah, I'm excited.
>> Pretty tasty.
>> It's a white meat.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I cannot believe I'm eating
lizard.
Oh, my God.
>> It kind of tastes like
chicken/fish.
>> What's he doing in there?
>> I'm looking.
I'm looking for the immunity
idol.
These people are so ignorant.
Everybody is standing in the
same spot.
I'm in a big old hole in the
tree and I don't want to look
suspicious but it surely does.
So I look in the tree, I look
up.
I almost passed out.
I seen it sitting there.
So I reached up there and
yanked it down, got it loose,
put it in my underwear, turned
around and just walked off.
The wonderful immunity idol.
Boo-yah.
>> Guess I'm on now, dude.
>> Ow!
Is that it?
>> When I looked up, I almost
passed out.
When I looked up and seen it, I
started shaking.
>> Keep it cool.
>> And then everybody's
standing right there!
>> I know.
How did you get it out of there,
put it in your pants?
>> Boo-ya.
>> Russell found the idol, so
I'm excited we have it.
I think it's definitely a tool
we can use.
>> Let me put it on before...
>> So "this is yours.
It can't be taken from you."
I'm not sure how I feel about
the fact that he has control of
it as opposed to me, but at
this point, I think I can trust
Russell a lot more.
You and I have still a deal?
>> Hell, yeah, dude, it's on.
I wouldn't have never told you
if it wouldn't have been.
I ain't stupid. So it's on.
>> Yeah, well let me get back
there before...
>> Okay.
>> We'll deal with that later.
My strategy from the beginning
was if I found the immunity
idol I wouldn't tell anybody,
but I wanted Jaison to trust
me, so I showed him I had it
and said, "You see.
You can trust me."
I don't have plans to give it
to him.
I just want him to think that I
will if he needs it.
How does it look on me?
Pretty?
>> Let's go get tree mail.
Come on.
>> Me and you?
>> Yes.
Okay, Mike, don't doubt
yourself.
We can do this, right?
We're not going to give up.
>> We got to. We got to.
Betsy's paranoid.
We're the two older ones, but
at Tribal Council, I didn't get
one vote but I want to show 'em
today that, you know, I'm not
the weakest.
I'm the oldest, but I am
definitely not the weakest.
>> We have to win challenges,
or we ain't good.
>> Right.
But I think that the next
challenge we're gonna do is
between Betsy and, you know,
Mike.
Whoever performs...
>> Right.
>> ...last, they're out.
>> Right. It's easy.
Next two are easy.
>> Easy, yup.
>> The debate about voting
people out is between Mike and
Betsy, and the more I thought
about it, the more I thought
that it would be smarter to vote
Mike off.
He can't compete physically,
and God forbid, if we lose the
next immunity, Mike's gonna go.
>> Mailman.
Take it, Boss.
>> Let's see what we got here.
"All the bravado and talking
smack may cost someone today.
"A rumble and a test of skill
will send one more away."
>> Physical.
>> "Rumble."
>> Rumble!
>> Yeah, baby!
(laughter)
>> Who's the boss?
Who's the boss?
>> "Come to the challenge
painted as a Samoan warrior."
Nice!
Who can draw?
>> I can draw.
>> Ben and I are drawing.
Whoo!
>> Mike's been dying for this
since day one.
>> This is the one where I have
to prove myself, show my stuff.
I'm a mean motor scooter and a
bad go-getter, man, when it
comes to one-on-one stuff.
>> They fight dirty around
here, Mike.
But you're from New York, I
know.
>> Someone's getting hurt, and
it ain't our team.
I'm going to take him downtown
to Chinatown, man.
I'm waiting for this.
Or I'll die trying.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Galu, getting your first look
at the new Foa Foa tribe.
Marisa voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
All right, you guys ready to
get to today's challenge?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
John, I'll take back the
immunity idol.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
On my "go," three members of
each tribe will battle to
retrieve three balls.
You'll pass those balls to
three other tribemates up on a
platform who will attempt to
shoot those balls into the
opposing tribe's basket.
After every point, we will
switch positions.
First tribe to score three
points wins immunity and
reward, and it's a nice one.
Fishing gear.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: If you cannot catch
fish with this, go home.
In addition, one other twist,
which will be revealed after
the challenge.
Make sense?
Galu, you have one extra member.
You're sitting somebody out,
cannot sit out the same person
in back-to-back challenges.
In this challenge, you must sit
out a woman.
Monica's going to sit this one
out.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize, and we'll
get started.
All right, first round.
In the pit, we have the men.
Up on the platform, the women
are the shooters.
Survivors ready?
Go!
A big collision right off the
bat.
You've got to get the ball to
the people on the platform so
they can take a shot at the
goal.
>> Rebound, rebound!
>> PROBST: Ball control is
everything in this game.
>> Throw it all the way!
>> PROBST: Shambo shoots and
misses.
Borassi getting in on it, goes
after Erik.
Russell has Brett tied up.
This is gonna be physical.
A lot on the line, this
challenge.
Borassi going after Erik again.
Laura goes underhand.
It's short, and Russell tied up.
Erik collides with Nick.
Liz shoots for Foa Foa and
scores!
(cheering and whooping)
Men, you're out, women, you're
down.
Next threesome, you're up on
the platform.
Foa Foa leads, one-zip.
Playing to three.
Survivors ready?
Go.
It's the women in the middle.
Laura and Natalie going at it
right away.
Jaison tries to pass it.
He's long.
John with a shot.
>> You ain't got nothin'!
>> PROBST: John is short.
Natalie and Laura with a heavy
match going.
Watch the choking.
No choking.
Russell with a shot for Galu.
Oh!
Shambo!
Easy on the face.
John with a shot.
John shoots and scores for Galu.
We are tied, one-one.
>> It's all right.
I know it's hard.
>> PROBST: All right, everybody
listen up.
I'm just gonna tell you what
I'm observing.
You're right on that line of
getting ugly, right on the line.
So there's no more warnings for
a head butt, an accidental
choke, a slap to the face.
Consider yourself warned that
from this point forward, if I
see anything resembling a cheap
shot, you're out of the
challenge.
Everybody good?
All right, we have our next
round.
Three men are on the platform,
two men, one woman in the pit.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Oh! Yasmin annihilates Ashley.
Russell and Jaison going at it.
Ben throws Yasmin into the
fence.
Erik with a shot.
Just misses.
Ben takes down John!
Russell and Jaison mix it up.
Everybody's tied up.
Mick with a shot for Foa Foa.
Brett with a shot for Galu.
A big battle on the ground.
Ben!
Stop!
Ben, out of the challenge!
(whooping)
First time in the history of
Survivor, somebody's been
pulled out of a challenge.
Take a spot here.
You're done.
>> You all right, Russ?
>> PROBST: Starting this point
over, Foa Foa is now down one
person.
That means here in the pit,
Galu has a huge advantage.
Two guys and a girl taking on
one guy and a girl.
We are still tied, one-one.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Galu has all three balls.
Big opportunity.
Jaison cannot get away from
Russell.
Jaison takes down John.
Erik with an underhand.
Erik scores for Galu!
Galu leads, two-one.
Next round.
Men, you're in the pit.
Women, up on the platform.
Foa Foa has to score to stay in
this challenge.
Galu scores, they win.
Survivors ready?
Go!
(yelling)
Oh! Dave and Russell collide in
the middle.
Borassi and Erik going at it.
Liz shoots and misses.
Oh!
Big bodies colliding.
Erik finally gets some payback
on Borassi.
>> Mike, get us the ball!
>> PROBST: Kelly just misses for
Galu.
Barossi still stunned from that
hit by Erik.
Laura goes underhand.
Laura scores for Galu!
(cheering)
Three-one-- Galu wins reward
and immunity!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Ben, how you feeling
about being the first person in
the history of this game to ever
be thrown out of a challenge?
>> Outlaw, baby.
Whatever.
No use crying over spilled milk.
I'm out.
I'm just gonna let it go.
>> PROBST: All right, Galu,
back-to-back immunity wins.
♪ ♪
Galu, safe from Tribal Council.
Huge reward of fishing gear,
plus one twist-- this involves
your leader.
Russell, come on over.
All right, as leader, you must
now select one person from your
tribe to accompany the other
tribe back to camp.
They will return back to your
camp after sitting in and
observing at Tribal Council.
Who you gonna send?
>> I'm going to send my home
girl... Yasmin.
>> PROBST: Yasmin, this is for
you.
Open in private once you get to
Foa Foa's camp.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Join Foa Foa.
After this challenge, this
should be interesting.
Galu, grab your fishing gear,
head on back to camp.
All right, Foa Foa, I will see
you once again at Tribal
Council.
And, Borassi, I want medical to
take a look at you.
>> You know, during the
challenge, Mike took some
really hard hits.
I mean, you know, he was very
out of breath.
I don't know, he just did not
seem right to me, and that's
huge, especially right now.
If we continue losing, we're
going to dwindle to nothing, and
then we're just gonna get
kicked out one by one.
(beeping)
>> What's his blood pressure
now?
>> 92 on 60.
And you want to stand up for me?
Okay.
How do you feel standing up?
>> A little woozy.
>> A little woozy?
All right. Hang on.
Cameron's there.
If you need to sit down...
>> Just keep that on.
>> When we were done with the
challenge, Mike was having
trouble breathing.
>> Just gonna get you to do some
deep breaths.
>> When medical checked him
out, he was suffering from
very, very low blood pressure.
>> I'm just gonna look at your
blood pressure again.
>> As a physician myself, you
always, especially out here,
you've got to consider the
worst-case scenario, which,
you know, for him is probably a
big heart attack.
>> Just have a tiny sit-up.
If you start feeling woozy at
all, I want you to lie straight
back down.
Cameron, can you...
>> I can do it on my own.
>> All right.
All right, we're going to take
it again.
It's 80 on 60.
So he's dropped 30 just
standing.
>> PROBST: Is this something
that a couple of canteens of
water back at camp will remedy?
>> We've already tried his
canteen, and we've waited for
the 40 minutes.
The fact that he was blue when
he came off the game is a bit
scary to start with, and it just
shows us that his heart's not
coping very well.
>> PROBST: So, Doc, just so
we're clear, you are pulling
Barossi from the game?
>> At this point, yes.
>> PROBST: Okay.
All right, Foa Foa, come say
your good-byes to Mike.
>> I wanted to go all the way,
you know?
I'm a little beat up, but...
those guys never got me down in
the pit.
>> Your health's worth way more
than a million bucks, my friend.
>> I think I showed that I can
be tough when I have to be, no
matter what age I am, you know?
>> PROBST: All right, so, here's
what this means.
Foa Foa is now down to eight
members.
You guys are going to head back
to camp with Yasmin.
You're still visiting.
You will still go to Tribal
Council tomorrow night.
You guys head back to camp.
Borassi, you're going to the
hospital.
>> I was privy to the
conversation that Mike had with
the physician there.
And I think she absolutely made
the right decision.
With Mike gone, Marisa gone,
and then a Tribal Council...
(sighs)
You know, I'd like to say we can
push through this, but it does
not bode well for us.
>> Did Shambo take the fins,
too?
>> I don't know.
>> Where is she?
>> I'd love her to come back
with fish.
Oh, she's way down there.
>> Shambo insisted that
spearfishing was her thing.
Awesome.
She's bringing back fish for
sure.
>> ♪ Coco rico in my belly. ♪
>> Yeah.
>> Shambo's been gone a while.
I hope that means she got some
fish.
>> This is the first bath I've
had in five days, even if it is
a swamp.
It feels awesome.
I didn't catch any fish, but I
tried.
And there's no visibility in
this pond water, so I can't use
the mask and the spear.
So I'm going to go Yogi Bear
back float around here for a
little while.
Hi, peeps.
>> Hey.
>> Hey. How'd it go?
>> You guys want the good news
or the bad news?
>> Bad news.
>> Bad news?
>> Yeah.
>> I had no luck in the ocean.
I was in the...
>> You broke the, uh...
>> I didn't break it.
It floated off while I was in
the swamp.
I wasn't using the mouthpiece.
I was using this... the mask.
>> Okay.
>> Just floated off.
>> So the mouthpiece is gone?
>> It is.
>> You couldn't find it?
>> It's in the swamp.
There's nothing I can do.
>> And the good news?
>> There are hundreds of
thousand of fish on the reef,
so...
>> The good news is-- you'll
never believe it-- there's fish
in the ocean.
You know, I feel sorry for her,
in one sense, because she's kind
of desperate right now, trying
to catch fish, and then on top
of not catching the fish, she
loses our stuff.
You just signed your own death
warrant is basically what you
did.
>> I mean, if everybody would
come closer, I'd like to
introduce myself.
>> Yeah.
>> Tell you guys who I am and
find out a little bit about you.
Okay, now, my name is Yasmin,
and I'm a professional hair
stylist.
I don't know how you're feeling
about me, but let's just say
I'm not the enemy.
Not only that; I'm here to help
you guys strategize, because to
me, I don't like a not-fair
fight.
It's almost like, why be matched
up with people that's not
matched up with the right
people, because then it's like
taking candy from a baby.
Who the hell wants to do that?
That don't boost my self-esteem.
You know what I'm saying?
That makes me seem like I
really did something that was a
cakewalk, but, um...
>> We got Yasmin here, and, uh,
what-what are her first words to
us?
"I want to help you guys. Why?
Because I don't want this to be
a cakewalk.
I don't want this to be like
taking candy from a baby."
I was, like, "Screw you."
>> Now don't get offended, but
personally, off the riff, I've
noticed that strategy may be,
um, something you guys are
lacking, and I don't know his
name.
What's his name right there?
>> Ben.
>> Ben, I would like to talk to
you in private about something.
For sure.
I know this is not the game that
people think you can be
honest...
>> She's full of crap.
She comes over here to our
camp, disrespects us, calls us
babies, tells us how we can win
a challenge if we listen to her.
She come to the wrong camp, and
she ain't getting nothing but
disrespect from me from now on,
and you know what?
She's going to pay for that
statement, I promise you.
>> "Congratulations.
You now have a clue to the
hidden immunity idol.
It's up to you whether you
share this information with
anyone else."
(sighs)
"Search hard here at Foa Foa.
Your treasure's not easy to see.
If you don't find it in a
little while, you must be
barking up the wrong tree."
Hmm.
I haven't been here all of two
hours yet, so I don't know who
I can trust.
I do care about getting that
idol, but with that clue and
all I had to go on was a tree.
You know how many trees are out
here?
Too many, so you know....
>> Sure.
>> Okay.
Now.
>> What's up?
>> Let's talk about cheap shots.
I don't know...
>> Trippin' somebody ain't a
cheap shot.
>> Uh, uh, uh, uh.
'Cause guess what?
You tackled me like a dude.
Don't tell me you don't
remember.
>> Well, that's just the way
the game's played.
It wasn't anything personal.
You were going after one of my
teammates...
>> But you a dude.
Look at the match-up.
Do you see women playing
football with men that play
football?
>> That's because they can't.
>> It's either all women...
>> They cannot...
>> I want to know.
They don't for a reason.
So I want to know, why would a
dude as tall as you tackle me?
>> 'Cause you were going after
my teammate.
>> That was very disrespectful.
>> Do you underst...
>> But... I understand what
you're saying, but you know
what?
You're not showing me no
sympathy, and you're not
understanding what I'm saying.
You're a dude.
It doesn't matter.
Yes, it is a game.
>> Listen, Grammar School.
Listen, here's where it's...
here's where it's going, all
right?
>> Listen, Ignorant, since you
want to say Grammar School.
>> Ignorant? What's the
definition of ignorant?
>> Yeah, yeah. What's the
definition of grammar school?
I'm just telling you how I feel.
But since I see I won't get
nowhere with you, I won't waste
my energy, but I wanted to let
you know because I don't back
down to nobody, and I don't
appreciate you tackling me.
>> You won't get anywhere with
me, not... no way.
Yasmin is just a piece of work.
Yasmin has a big mouth.
Yasmin smells bad.
She's got really poor grammar.
I think Yasmin is pretty close
to being a hooker.
>> You the one look like a fool.
You look like a big jerk going
after a girl.
Okay, if a dude saw that on TV,
they wouldn't say, "Ooh, he
tackled a girl; he's the bomb."
They'd be, like, "You know what?
He's a big sissy."
That's what they would say.
>> I say, "Kill 'em all."
I say, "Kill 'em all."
>> That's what they would say,
but you heard what I said.
>> Yeah, I heard your incorrect
grammar the whole time.
>> Uh-huh.
>> She was just barking up the
wrong tree, 'cause I'm the one
person that you just don't want
to approach like that.
>> And I see, you know what?
>> You don't even know the
definition of ignorant.
>> You're looking for a fight
because you're ignorant.
>> You don't even know the
definition of ignorant.
>> Who would tackle a girl that
weighs 110?
>> You were going after my
teammate, so just shut up.
You're in our camp.
>> Ben is definitely a wild
card.
He's definitely a liability.
He's saying things at
challenges.
He's getting kicked out of
Um, honestly, I think what Ben's
doing is stupid on his part.
>> She's ghetto trash, plain
and simple.
>> That's right.
>> She needs to go back to
eating ketchup sandwiches and
drinking Kool-Aid and doing
whatever the hell she does and
leave me alone.
>> You know what?
I wish Yasmin was here for
another three days 'cause I love
confrontation.
'Cause her and Ben start
fighting.
Everybody starts hearing it.
I love that.
That just makes everybody not
like Ben.
You know, I got some great
plans set ahead, and, uh, it's
going to be real fun.
(scraping)
>> What do you think?
(animal hooting, birds singing)
>> Um, I don't know what's
going on, but Ben was up all
night.
I think he's asking to be thrown
out.
It was so ridiculous.
It was so crazy.
Why would you hammer a machete
in the middle of the night?
With a fire going.
There's no reason.
So I don't think anybody's too
happy.
>> I was getting really annoyed
by the guy, and it's really
starting to drive me crazy.
>> You know how he gets, man.
Anybody calls him out on
anything, or he gets
exasperated, he really just
unleashes, instead of just being
like, "Hey, man we need to talk
about this."
>> Who the hell hammers in the
middle of the night?
At nothing.
>> I don't know.
>> I don't get him.
Now that Mike's gone, my head
is definitely on the chopping
block, 'cause I know they're
all looking at me as being the
elder and the weakest.
But I don't want to go home at
all.
I don't want to go home at all.
Ben needs to go, in my opinion.
I know that you're saying, "Oh,
we need him for strength or to
win challenges," but we haven't
won any challenges, and plus, he
got kicked out of a challenge.
So, I would have voted for him.
Even if it didn't happen last
night and all that, I was going
to vote for him anyway.
I was going to tell you I was
going to vote for him.
>> Tonight, I think Betsy's
going home.
We need to focus on challenges,
and she is considered to be the
weakest link right now,
physically.
But, uh, Ben getting kicked out
of the challenge, him waking up
and chopping wood, his big
altercation with, uh, Yasmin-- I
mean, those are three big
strikes, so I don't know if
he's got a lot of friends left.
>> Go with your gut.
Go with a woman's intuition.
>> It's hard.
>> It's strong, though.
Listen to your intuition.
To go to a... go with a
police woman, motherly type, or
an outlaw?
>> I don't know.
There's a lot at stake.
>> An outlaw who is a pain in
the ass!
I think if anybody else got
kicked out of a challenge--
which has never happened
before-- they would be getting
voted off at Tribal Council.
Why isn't it not Ben?
>> Just I don't know.
>> I won't write your names
down.
>> Maybe Ben would be the right
choice to kick out tonight.
He's not a nice guy, and he's,
you know, kind of pissing people
off.
I did originally think, you
know, I was stuck on voting out
Betsy, but now that I think
about it more and more, I don't
know if that's the right choice.
>> I just don't know if we're
making the right choice.
>> Well, this is... this is my
thing.
We made a big sacrifice with
Marisa and we kept the physical
weakness, and we lost.
>> Well, and we got a loss
because he got thrown out of the
challenge yesterday.
>> Yes, absolutely.
>> And he's pissing a lot of
people off around camp.
Yeah, he might be physically a
little better, but Betsy's a
cop.
And you know what, if we...
>> But she's slow.
>> There are some good points to
voting off Ben eventually, but
Betsy is a 47-year-old cop and
Ben is a 28-year-old... young
guy.
They are not physically
equivalent, which is the
argument that Ashley was trying
to make.
And I'm, like, oh, my God.
I can't... I don't know what to
do with this girl.
I think it's more better for you
to talk to Ashley.
>> Well, what is she so
concerned about?
She's trying to switch up the
whole thing.
>> She's getting worried, and
you need to, like, lock and
load.
>> Wow.
>> I don't know.
>> Betsy has to go, or we will
get our asses kicked.
It's over.
She's going, for sure.
>> You and I know that...
>> You... you...
Jaison...
She... you know what?
She better stop that.
>> I didn't talk to her.
>> Betsy's going home tonight
because, first of all, she's the
weakest link, and second of all,
she doesn't trust me.
Marissa threatened me, Betsy
threatened me-- I'm gonna go
down the line.
Each time somebody threatens me,
they're going home.
Ashley-- she'll be going home
next.
I want to keep Ben this time,
and you know what?
Ben's gonna stay this time.
'Cause whatever I want, happens.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in and take a
seat.
Yasmin, you can have a seat
right over here.
All right, last time you were
here, the discussion really
centered around a negative force
that you identified as Marisa.
You voted her out.
Liz, one big happy family now?
>> Uh, I think so, for the most
part.
It doesn't help that we lost yet
another challenge.
That never bodes well, but I
think going forward, yeah, we
are pretty united.
>> PROBST: So if it's one big
happy family, Yasmin's visit
must have been fairly pleasant?
>> Um, there was one minor
incident with Yasmin and Ben,
but I think for the most part,
her stay was fairly congenial.
>> PROBST: Ben, what happened
with Yasmin?
>> Uh, when Yasmin showed up,
she said, "Let's talk about
cheap shots."
She goes, "Oh, you tackled me,
and I'm a girl."
I'm, like, "There wasn't any
rule that a guy couldn't push a
girl down."
And she's, like, "Oh, you're a
sissy," and, like, starts going
on and on and on.
Her grammar is so poor, it was
like talking to an idiot.
She's ghetto trash, and I have
no respect for her and she needs
to go back to where she came
from.
>> PROBST: Russell, you're
biting your tongue to get in on
this.
>> I have to say, when she came
to our house, she said, "It's
like taking candy from a baby."
If somebody came to your house
and disrespected your family,
are you gonna turn the other
cheek and go in the other room,
or are you gonna kick 'em out
your house?
>> Well, I think we can sit here
and talk about kicking somebody
out of the house, but we got to
win a challenge.
Yeah, I was upset that she said
"taking candy from a baby," and
I don't want to get punched in
the face and left in the mud and
then been told that I'm a baby,
no.
But, you know, you don't prove
it in here, you don't prove it
by yelling at somebody-- you
prove it by beating the other
team, period.
>> PROBST: Mick, you're the
leader.
You okay with how Ben handles
defending your tribe?
>> That's how Benny rolls,
basically.
I mean, the guy doesn't just
show teeth, I mean, he bites.
>> PROBST: Can that be
disruptive to a tribe?
>> Well, I think it sort of
intimidates people a little bit.
But you know what you're gonna
get from him, so if you don't
want that, like, don't go there.
>> I'd just like to say
something about Ben.
>> PROBST: Betsy.
>> With him helping us lose the
challenge, him mouthing off, him
chopping wood in the middle of
the night, driving everybody
crazy, he would probably be the
first person being voted out
tonight.
And what I don't understand is,
I'm the only one that brought my
bag.
And maybe it's the cop, but we
have one of these guys in
every town.
It's, like, "Did you see that
speeder go by?
He was going faster than I was."
You know? It's where they just
basically slide by the rules.
I mean, if I got kicked out of a
challenge yesterday, I could
understand, but I don't
understand why my head's on the
chopping block and not his.
>> PROBST: Ashley, you think it
hurt you guys yesterday losing
Ben?
>> Definitely.
I was in there with two guys and
a girl, and they'd attack
Jaison, so it was just me.
So it did hurt us in the end,
which is disappointing, but...
>> PROBST: Ben, any regret at
all about what happened at the
challenge?
>> First of all, you never said
we were playing by your kind of
sissy rules.
I mean, I regret that I didn't
get to help my teammates, but do
I regret tripping him?
Absolutely not.
I mean, everybody else is doing
all this really crazy stuff,
and all I did was trip somebody.
>> PROBST: Accidental trip or on
purpose?
>> Oh, completely on purpose.
I was, like, "This guy's big; I
can't tackle him.
But guess what?
My legs are longer than his.
Whack! Big tree fall hard."
That's basically what happened.
>> PROBST: Ben, say that when
this game started you had a 100%
chance of winning.
Where do you think it's at now?
>> I got a good as chance as
anybody.
>> PROBST: You believe, based on
how you've acted, that your
chances of winning are as good
as anybody else left in the
game?
>> I definitely do.
You know what, I'm
straightforward people.
And I'm one of those people, I
do not start a fight, but if you
come at me, you're gonna get a
fight.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
get to the vote.
That means, Yasmin, your time
here is done.
You've had a chance to observe a
lot.
What you choose to share and
what you choose to keep to
yourself is up to you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
All right, it is time to vote.
Mick, you're up.
>> ♪ Bad boy, bad boy
Whatcha gonna do
When they come for you? ♪
Don't use my name if you ever
get stopped in New Hampshire.
>> I thought you were a good
cop, but you're a bad cop, so
this one's for you.
(imitates gunshot)
(exhales sharply)
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Betsy.
Ben.
One vote Betsy, one vote Ben.
Betsy.
Two votes Betsy, one vote Ben.
That's three votes Betsy, one
vote Ben.
Betsy.
That's four votes Betsy, one
vote Ben.
The second person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa...
Betsy.
That's five; that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Betsy, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
♪ ♪
Well, it's clear from tonight's
Tribal Council that you are
voting together.
The question is, are you working
together?
Six days in, down three
members-- something not working
right.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
Russell's mind games continue.
>> You plant that seed in their
head, and it's called a "Russell
seed."
It takes over their whole mind.
>> PROBST: Jaison recruits an
army to fight him.
>> I'm definitely loyal to
Jaison.
>> PROBST: And Shambo is on the
outs.
>> Are you frickin' kidding me?
You know, we got four people
doing yoga.
>> Well, it took me six years to
get here.
I loved every minute of it.
The only thing I'm not gonna
miss is Ben and his attitude.
He needs to grow up.
He's still not admitting that he
did something wrong at the
challenge.
It's all gonna blow up in their
face.
They made the wrong choice
tonight.
I just hope they kind of see
that.
If they don't open up their
eyes, the whole tribe will go
down, I bet.