>> JEFF PROBST: 27 days ago, two
tribes of ten castaways each
began an epic battle.
The purple tribe, Galu, won
almost every encounter.
Galu wins immunity!
By the time the two tribes
merged, the yellow tribe, Foa
Foa, was down to four.
The old Galu had eight, and
they planned to keep it that
way.
>> What's Samoan for "Get the
hell off my island"?
>> Look at us.
We're like savages.
>> PROBST: But the old Foa Foa
losses sharpened their ability
to strategize.
>> Things are about to change
totally in this game.
I don't think they even realize
it right now.
We're steps ahead of them.
We already have our plan down.
>> PROBST: And the plan worked.
At the next two Tribal
Councils, two of the old Galu
went home.
But the old Foa Foa paid a
price-- Russell had to play his
hidden immunity idol.
Then three game-changing
events took place.
One, Russell found another
hidden immunity idol.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Two, Shambo agreed
to vote with the Foa Foa four
to take out Laura.
>> It is the destiny of Laura
to go home.
>> PROBST: And, three, John
agreed to switch his vote,
hoping that Russell would vote
out a Foa Foa next.
>> Next one needs to be Foa Foa.
Deal?
>> Okay. That's a deal.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
John changed his vote.
The ninth person voted out and
the third member of our jury.
And Laura made it three of the
old Galus in a row.
>> PROBST: And now, the entire
tribe is about to find out if
the old Foa Foa is as good at
holding on to a lead as they are
at getting one.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(chickens clucking)
>> Medusa has been dethroned.
Is that just hysterical?
(snickering)
>> At Tribal tonight, Laura
went home.
The vote was 5-5.
The rules of Survivor say that
if there is another tie after a
second round of voting, the
remaining members would choose
rocks.
One of those rocks would be of
a different color, and that
person would go home.
I'm not going to go home
because of ridiculous rocks.
I gave multiple, multiple
explanations and multiple
rationale for why we should be
making different decisions, and
no dice.
I had a conversation with
Russell in which he and I said
the next person to go would be
Foa Foa.
So right now, I think I have a
pretty good position.
What's funny is, collectively,
they made the correct move, and
I made the correct move.
>> We all want to make it to
the end, but at some point, you
need to show loyalty and
integrity and respect for the
people that you made promises
to.
When it came down to it
tonight...
>> Uh-huh.
>> I still could not flop for
Laura.
I definitely have come to see
John as little bit more as a
Judas of the Galu tribe.
Then John has to go home.
♪ ♪
>> Tree mail.
>> Oh, happy day!
>> Oh, y'all going to be happy
about this.
You might as well get up.
>> Is it food?
>> You're kidding me, dude!
>> Open it up first.
>> Eh.
>> Oh!
(belly-laugh)
>> Cold cash money!
>> Yeah!
(cheering)
>> "Going once, going twice,
gone.
This should be some fun.
Play is right and you just may
have a full belly by the time
it's done."
>> Food auction!
>> We just got a tree mail.
We got money, baby!
Money means food, so I'm really
excited about that 'cause I'm
literally starving.
So I know definitely I'm eating
off my muscle of my body, so
today is a really good day.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
I love seeing so many smiles.
(laughter)
Welcome to the Survivor
auction.
You've each been given $500.
Bidding will be in increments
of $20.
There is no sharing of money.
No sharing of food.
Auction will end without
warning.
If you see something you like,
bid on it.
Ready to get started?
>> ALL: Yes.
>> PROBST: First item.
Shall I uncover it or cover it?
>> ALL: Uncover it.
>> PROBST: Peanut butter and
jelly sandwich.
>> Ooh.
>> $200.
(Dave whistles)
>> Holy cow!
>> PROBST: Natalie, knowing
that the bidding goes in
increments of $20, jumps to
$200.
>> Yes.
>> She just bought herself a
peanut butter and jelly
sandwich, Jeff.
>> It's yours, Nat.
>> PROBST: $200 going once,
twice.
(gavel bangs)
Sold to Natalie.
Come on up.
All right, Natalie, $200 bought
you a PB & J.
Take a little bite right here.
>> Oh, my goodness.
Look at all this peanut butter.
Mmm!
Totally worth the $200.
>> PROBST: All right, take it
back. Enjoy it.
>> Thank you.
(Monica gasps)
>> Wow!
>> That has a lot of peanut
butter in it!
>> Good girl.
>> PROBST: Next item will remain
covered.
>> $80.
>> PROBST: $80 to Jaison.
>> $100.
$100 to Monica.
>> $120.
>> $140.
>> $120 to John, $140 to Jaison.
>> $200.
>> PROBST: $200 to Shambo.
$200.
>> I'll go $220.
>> PROBST: $220 to Dave.
>> $240.
>> PROBST: $240 to Shambo.
Going once, twice.
(gavel bangs)
Sold to Shambo.
$240 for the mystery item.
>> What did I get?
>> PROBST: Give me the money
first.
>> Okay, baby.
>> Show me the money!
>> Done.
>> PROBST: $240 bought you a
Survivor version of spaghetti.
>> Oh, really?
>> PROBST: Sea noodles and slug
guts.
>> ALL: Aw...
>> Oh, dude!
>> PROBST: To go.
>> Yum! Thank you.
>> PROBST: With a little bit of
parmesan.
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: To bring out the
flavor.
>> Good stuff.
>> Oh, man!
>> Huh.
>> Does it have, like,
nutritional starch value, do
you know?
>> PROBST: I don't.
>> God, I hope it does 'cause
my body is really deprived.
>> PROBST: Let's just say it
does.
All right, Shambo.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Enjoy.
Next item.
It's so much fun to keep them
covered.
>> $300.
>> PROBST: Right off the bat,
Dave Ball says $300...
for a covered item.
>> $320.
>> They're playing... They're
playing the odds right now.
>> $340.
>> PROBST: What are the chances
we would put back-to-back bad
items?
>> Very, very strong chances.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That's what I think.
>> PROBST: Monica at $340.
Going once, going twice.
Sold to Monica for $340.
>> I hope this is good, Jeff.
>> PROBST: So do I.
(laughter)
>> Please, please, please,
please, please be good.
>> PROBST: Well, it cost you a
lot.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: I hope you think it
was worth it.
>> Oh!
(Monica laughs)
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: A whole roasted
chicken.
>> Oh! Oh, my God!
>> Damn!
>> Wow!
(Dave laughs)
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh, gee.
>> PROBST: Next item.
This is a significant advantage
in the next immunity challenge.
>> Hundj.
>> PROBST: $100 to John.
>> $140.
>> $140 to Natalie.
>> $200.
>> PROBST: $200 to John.
You have a one in nine shot in
this game right now.
This could make it one in eight.
>> $260.
>> PROBST: Jaison in on it at
$260.
>> $300.
>> PROBST: $300 to John.
>> I thought, uh, when John was
bidding on the item that would
do well in the challenge that
we needed to be in possession
of that item.
Maybe it was my turn to, you
know, sacrifice a little bit for
the good of the former Foa Foa.
I... Can I ask you a question
before I bid?
We both have 500 bucks.
What if we both bid $500?
>> PROBST: Somebody's going to
get to $500 first.
>> Yeah.
>> So it's whoever gets to $500
first?
>> PROBST: Yeah.
>> 500 bucks.
>> PROBST: 500 bucks.
>> All right, Jaison!
>> PROBST: Sold to Jaison.
>> Playing like a true lawyer.
>> PROBST: Keep this sealed.
Bring it to the next immunity
challenge.
You will open it there.
We'll find out if it was worth
it.
>> Nice move.
>> PROBST: So Jaison spends all
his money on one item, and that
means no food.
Next item.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my word!
>> $500.
>> Mick, yeah!
Get them!
>> PROBST: Wow!
Mick just closed down the
bidding with one bid of $500.
>> Here you go.
>> PROBST: Sold to Mick as
Jaison buries his head in his
hands.
>> Good job, Mick.
>> Oh, my God, that was
hilarity.
>> PROBST: That's a
cheeseburger, fries, ketchup,
mustard...
>> Ugh!
>> PROBST: ...cold beer. Enjoy.
>> Thank you.
>> Holy cow!
(Jaison groans)
>> Nice job, bro.
>> PROBST: Jaison?
>> Yeah?
>> PROBST: Second thoughts?
>> Sitting here right now and
seeing you uncover that thing,
yeah, second, third, fourth,
fifth, tenth thoughts, like, "I
want that hamburger.
I want it badly."
(Shambo laughs)
>> PROBST: Next item.
A clue to the location of the
hidden immunity idol.
>> $100.
>> $120.
>> $200.
>> PROBST: $120 to Natalie.
$200 to John.
Only one thing keeps you safe
in this game, and that is
immunity.
$200 to John.
Going once, going twice.
Sold to John.
>> Nice job, Johnnie.
>> Nice one, buddy.
>> Excuse moi.
Russell may have the idol, you
know.
Anyone can.
>> PROBST: Take it with you.
Open this back at camp.
>> I'm not going to sit here and
go, "I'm gonna let the immunity
go.
Someone else can buy that."
Absolutely not.
Immunity is the goal.
>> PROBST: Next item-- you've
been looking at it.
It's the Survivor shower.
>> $100.
>> PROBST: Which John has bid
$100 on already.
Shampoo, conditioner, clean
underwear.
>> Clean underwear.
$120.
>> PROBST: $100 to John.
$120 to Natalie.
>> Go ahead and get in there,
girl.
>> PROBST: $120 to Natalie going
once, twice.
Sold to Natalie-- $120.
>> Oh, do it, girl.
>> No one wants to see old John
take a shower.
>> PROBST: Here's your towel.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Enjoy your shower.
>> Oh, yes.
Oh, my goodness.
>> Whoo!
(laughter)
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> PROBST: Next item-- let's
uncover.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: One gigantic piece of
apple pie.
>> $180.
>> $300.
>> PROBST: $180 to Brett.
$300 to John.
Going once, going twice.
$300-- sold to John.
>> Why's it always got to be
apple pie, my favorite?
Can't be something else.
>> PROBST: $300.
Now, that is what you bought.
That is yours.
You can keep that.
Before you dig into it, I'll
give you an option.
You can choose right now to keep
that piece of pie for yourself,
or you can give up your piece of
pie.
You will have no pie, and you
can divvy up among four people
an entire pie.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> PROBST: Do you remain
selfish, keep this for
yourself, or do you try to buy
some good will?
>> Well, what's the move?
What do you guys want?
Is anyone really stoked on pie?
>> Yes, I'm stoked on pie.
>> I love pie.
>> It's your move, man.
>> It's your choice.
It's your move, dude.
>> It sucks that this was my--
you know, there's always a
choice, but I'll eat the pie.
Everyone's nice and I'm
confident that no one's going to
vote me off because they didn't
get a piece of apple pie.
>> PROBST: Enjoy.
>> John should have gave the pie
to everybody.
It just showed how stingy he
was.
You're playing a game.
You're in the game.
You don't need to eat.
If it was me, I would have gave
it to my tribe-- Foa Foa-- and
Shambo, so I think it was a
terrible move.
It was terrible at that point in
the game.
>> PROBST: All right, that's
going to be it.
The Survivor auction is over.
>> This morning I got a clue to
the hidden immunity idol, so
that's something that can help
me advance in this game and
potentially, you know, guarantee
me passage at least past the
next Tribal Council.
I'm hoping, you know, knock on
wood, that this is a pretty good
clue.
"The immunity idol is no rolling
stone.
At a fork in the road you'll see
a structure of rocks.
Which are covered with a blanket
of green.
So search at the base, you may
dirty your hands.
Remember, it's hidden, so it's
not easily seen."
I'm assuming it's buried.
I'm not seeing it right now.
I don't know if anyone had been
in here.
Everything outside is disturbed,
so it could be found already.
It's making me wonder if Russell
has the idol.
I mean, he's good at finding
idols without clues, but I'm
still going to make moves to
advance myself in this game.
Better safe than sorry.
I'll keep looking.
(chickens clucking)
>> We're going to have to have
you guys for lunch today, and I
just wanted to let you know,
okay?
(chicken squawks)
Well, I'll talk to you in Heaven
when I go to Heaven, okay?
Bye, chickens.
The chickens were probably my
single source of happiness the
last 29 days.
>> We can all take a hand in it.
>> I can't do it.
I won't do it.
I'll start bawling because I'm
really attached to those
chickens.
We'd have conversations and I'd
tell them, "I really need you
guys to lay me some eggs because
all these people want to kill
you."
And they'd go...
(squawks)
...like they understood and they
knew exactly what I was saying.
(chickens clucking)
I think that I brought them as
much peace as they brought me,
and it was a win-win.
Then... off with their heads.
(chickens clucking, Russell
mumbling)
(clucking stops)
>> You got him.
>> That actually wasn't so bad.
>> Mm-mm.
>> Tell me when the chickens
stop screaming.
What I'm going to do is I'm
gonna part the chickens out, and
I'm going to boil them in a
little bit of salt water and a
lot of fresh water.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Can we rotisserie at least
one?
So we can get some, like...
>> No, absolutely not.
>> Why?
>> Because you'll lose 65%
yield.
I'll take care of the cooking
because I might not know a lot
about a lot of things, but when
it comes to cooking... that's
time to say "shut up" if you're
me.
>> I think most people just want
to skewer the chicken and put it
over the fire, but Shambo, being
the chef and all that, is going
to, like, want to do something
crazy, and so I-- you know, we
don't even care so long as we're
eating chicken today.
So I think that's the plan
unless somebody decides to veto
it later.
>> How's that chicken coming?
>> About another hour and a
half.
(Dave whistles)
>> Yeah, um, that's a hard boil.
>> Yeah, we're not having a
conversation about the soup this
time, everybody, 'cause I'm in
no mood, so just trust me.
We'll just call it a bad case of
PMS, but I'm really in no mood
to talk about the soup today.
>> I won those chickens, Shambo,
so I think I should be able to
say something.
>> You go right ahead 'cause I'm
not listening.
>> You boil a chicken for two
hours, it's going to be ruined.
>> You have no idea what the
(bleep) you're talking about
right now and you got to just
respect that on some level.
>> Okay, cool.
>> I don't think I have been
more angry in the last 29 days,
truthfully.
He really snapped my head off my
body.
To have him walk up to me and
say, "What's going on with the
chicken?
Are they done?"
I went, "Red code, emergency
alert.
Shannon has lost her mind."
He has absolutely no idea who
he's picking a fight with today.
♪ ♪
(chickens clucking)
It's crazy 'cause I think God
made me really special.
In my lifetime, I've had some
dreams about situations that I'm
pondering, and sometimes it's
dreams that are just out of the
blue that occur, and they're,
they're literally clairvoyant
dreams.
I've probably had, I don't know,
30 of them in my lifetime, and I
think that's God's divine
intervention at work.
I don't know what makes me think
that.
I just-- it's-- I really, truly
believe that.
I think that's what it is, I
really do, and I had a dream
last night we voted Dave off.
(chickens clucking)
Dave is the first to go.
>> Set in stone, set in stone.
>> Set in freaking stone.
Deal?
>> Deal.
>> He's gone.
>> Shambo had a dream that they
voted off Dave.
I said, "That's a sign, Shambo.
That's a sign.
That's like God talking to you."
(laughs)
So she has her dreams who she's
voting off, and then that's who
it has to be.
We've got somebody unstable like
Shambo.
All she votes with is her
emotions.
You make her mad at somebody,
that's it.
She'll vote for them.
>> Oh, my word.
>> Once Dave's gone, we have the
numbers.
I'll run it all the way to the
top.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Mick, give it up.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
each have a rope and a very
heavy log.
Your job-- hold on to that log
for as long as you can.
Every three minutes, you'll
switch hands and move one knot
lower on the rope.
This will dramatically increase
the amount of weight pulling on
your arm.
When you can't hold on to the
log any longer, the log drops,
you're out of the challenge.
Last person standing wins
immunity, guaranteed a one in...
>> Eight.
>> PROBST: ...eight shot at a
million dollars.
At the auction, Jaison, you
spent all of your money on one
item, and that item was a
significant advantage in today's
challenge.
Go ahead and open up the bottle
and read the note.
>> All right, it says, "At any
point during today's immunity
challenge, you may move your
hand up two knots on the
rope..."
(Dave whistles)
..."giving you a significant
advantage."
>> PROBST: So what that means--
at any time, you can move up two
full knots, which will
significantly reduce the tension
and the amount of weight you're
holding.
Time it right, it will be a huge
advantage.
Could be the difference in this
challenge.
Take your spots.
We will get started.
All right, everybody grab a hold
with your right hand...
the first section of rope.
Each time we move down a section
of rope, you are going to feel
it.
These logs weigh as much as you
do.
This challenge is on.
(rope creaking)
Every three minutes, you'll
switch to the other hand.
You will only have one hand on
this rope at any given time.
All right, everybody place your
left hand on the second position
on the rope.
Get a good grip and release
your right hand.
Hot day to be sitting out in the
sun holding on to a heavy log.
All right, everybody put your
left hand on the fourth position
on the knot.
>> Now I'm using both.
>> PROBST: Jaison using his two
spots right now.
Jaison is now only on the second
knot.
Everybody else is on the fourth
Jaison used that move very early
in this challenge.
See if it pays off.
All right, everybody, it is time
to move further down on the
rope.
Three, two, one.
Release.
Now the log's going to begin to
get heavy.
Shambo trying to hold on.
(glass breaking)
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Shambo.
The log and Shambo take a
tumble.
Shambo, first person out of this
challenge.
You all right?
>> I'm good to go.
(glass breaking)
>> PROBST: Russell, surprisingly
drops out.
What happened?
>> I got a charley horse in my
forearm, and that was it.
>> PROBST: All right, everybody,
it is time to make the last
move.
Switch hands.
Three, two, one.
And release.
You have no knot now to give
you any kind of leverage or any
kind of grip.
Now this rope can slip through
your hands a lot more easily.
Jaison, on the other hand, does
have a knot to hold on to, and
now will never feel all of the
weight of this log.
(rope creaking)
(glass breaking)
Monica drops her log.
>> All right, go ahead, boys.
(glass breaking)
>> PROBST: John's had enough.
He steps out of the challenge.
(glass breaking)
Brett cannot hold on any longer.
Brett is out of the challenge.
We are down to four-- Jaison,
Dave, Mick and Natalie.
I have to say, Natalie, you've
got to be the surprise of this
challenge right now.
(glass breaking)
Mick drops out of the challenge.
We are down to three.
We have two former Foa Foa, one
former Galu.
Everybody doing a good job of
digging deep.
Keep digging.
You have more in there.
You never know when it's your
turn to go.
You don't want it to be tonight.
(Jaison exhales loudly)
(rope creaking)
That hand better be bleeding
when you let go.
(glass breaking)
Natalie cannot hang in there any
longer.
>> Darn.
>> PROBST: Great effort.
Natalie out of the challenge.
And we are down to two, side by
side-- Jaison and Dave for
immunity.
Jaison has a two-knot advantage.
Dave Ball is holding on to rope
with no knot.
It could easily slip through his
hands.
(rope creaking)
>> You got it, Jaison.
>> PROBST: Dave with a bit of a
slip.
>> He's slipping.
>> Hang on, Jais.
>> Hang on.
(rope creaking)
(glass breaking)
>> PROBST: Dave Ball cannot hold
on any longer.
Jaison wins individual immunity!
>> Good job, Dave.
(glass breaking)
>> Yeah.
>> Good job.
>> When Dave's hand slipped and
the plate broke, it was like
heaven.
I mean, I'm not sure I would
have beaten Dave without that
advantage.
Shambo wants him gone, and the
former Foa Foa are trying to
strike while the iron is hot
with Shambo.
I just want to focus and
execute.
We've got to get Dave tonight.
>> PROBST: Jaison, come on over.
>> Victory!
>> Good job, Jaison.
>> Yay, Jaison!
>> Finally won something.
>> Finally you won!
>> Finally wins!
>> Great job, Jaison!
>> PROBST: Well, you passed up
chicken.
>> It cost me food and money,
yeah.
>> PROBST: You passed up
cheeseburger, but while
everybody else has a full belly,
you have something much more
valuable-- safety at tonight's
Tribal Council.
Jaison cannot be voted out.
As for the rest of you, after 30
days out here, one of you going
home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> I am definitely in a position
of power with Foa Foa at my
disposal to vote how I ask them
to.
And they keep saying, "Shannon,
whatever you want."
Dave is so gone, he doesn't even
know it.
>> Man, good job today.
>> Dave, good work.
You almost beat me, and you had
no knot.
That's incredible.
>> You beat me fair and square,
bro.
>> Hey, awesome.
>> Well, I had...
>> Hey, you, too. Good job.
>> That was good.
>> You're on fire, man.
>> Thanks, man, thanks.
>> What were you doing up there?
Just think... just keep...?
>> Dave made a few comments to
Shambo about the chicken and how
to cook it and stuff, and she
was furious, and, you know, when
she gets sort of angry at
somebody, that's who she wants
voted off, but at this point, we
kind of count on Shambo's votes,
so it's going to be Dave.
>> Thank you.
I'm bummed I lost, but, oh,
well.
>> It was nice, man.
>> You and me finally won
something, huh? Back to back.
>> I know, look at that.
>> I know...
>> C'est la vie.
C'est la vie.
>> No way. No way.
>> Clearly, Galu is running
scared.
>> Right.
>> The next vote, I can get them
to vote off someone from
Foa Foa.
>> Right.
>> You already said you were
cool with that.
>> Right.
>> So I think we just lay low,
we hang out, not a lot...
>> So, right now, just, uh, I
guess we're thinking Mick right
now.
>> I mean, I think... I think
so, man.
>> It might be the best option,
uh, both ways, yeah.
>> And then we continue to move
on and move on and move on and
move on through this game and
progress further and further.
>> Right.
>> And if something crazy
happens, because you have ears
here and I have ears there...
>> Yeah, I'll let you know.
>> If we are... If we do find
ourselves outgunned, we can see
it coming...
>> Right.
>> ...we play the idol, and
then we're done.
>> You have it.
I'm 100% sure...
>> Where-Where... Where'd you
look?
>> Uh... well, I...
>> Tell me where the clue was,
and I'll tell you, I'll give
you a hint.
>> What do you mean?
>> Tell me where the clue was,
and I'll tell you where the
idol is.
At first, we were thinking, get
rid of Dave.
Everybody's on board to get rid
of Dave.
It was in the wall 'cause it
didn't roll off.
>> Yeah. Right, right.
>> So, it was sitting inside.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> In the meantime, probably the
best move would be to get rid of
John.
He's a threat strategically,
and, uh... and I told him that I
had the immunity idol.
And I go, "Good for me..."
>> Right.
>> "...if anyone has it, 'cause
I thought about the numbers.'
>> I knew he knew I had it.
So he said, "I know you have
it."
So I didn't want to sit there--
"No, I don't, no, I don't."
So I said, "Yeah, I have it,
and it can help us."
So now, I have to get rid of
John.
>> As long as you give me your
word that you're not voting for
me, we're both here after the
vote, we can continue to work...
>> Right.
These poor people need to close
their ears when I start talking,
'cause when I tell you
something, and I made a mistake,
I got to get rid of you.
It was my mistake, but, sorry,
John, you've got to go home for
it.
Sounds good to me, man, as long
as, uh, we stick together...
>> I mean, you're not going to
burn me the next vote, I'm not
gonna burn you the next vote.
I'm mean, we're rolling.
>> Yeah, as long as we stick
together, then we can do this,
the whole way through.
>> So we're fine.
>> All right, cool.
I can save you tonight.
It would be you.
>> It would be me?
>> It would definitely.
>> I had a feeling.
>> Now, it's going to be Shambo,
and the whole Foa Foa tribe.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That's whose the vote is.
>> Okay.
>> I think the best way to do
this is get rid of John tonight.
And there's no reason I would be
lying about this...
>> Mm.
>> ...because why would I come
to you saying, I want to get rid
of him when your name's in the
sling right now?
>> Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
>> Is-Is Monica close to John?
Can you tell her without her
going to John and saying
anything?
>> I could probably say
something to her.
>> All right.
>> Uh, yeah, yeah, well, you
know what, is-- I mean, after
he, uh, flipped on Laura, a
matter of frigging time.
You know, nobody trusts him
anymore.
>> It will be you if it's not
John.
I want you to stay in the game.
>> All right.
Because I almost won it today,
huh?
>> That was pretty impressive.
>> All right.
>> I don't want them to see me
talking to you too much.
>> All right.
All right, brother.
>> All right, man.
>> All right.
>> If you had a choice to get
rid of anybody in this game
right now, who would it be?
>> John.
>> He is dangerous.
>> Most dangerous person here.
>> With him gone, things would
be... we could run it down.
>> Oh, dude, it'd be cake.
>> Dave is way too scared right
now to not make this deal.
Way too scared.
We just talked for about 30
minutes.
>> You did?
I don't know, what do you
think, man?
I think we try John.
>> I think we get rid of John.
>> What happens next week with
Dave gone?
What is Shambo going to do?
We don't know.
Dude, I don't trust them.
I don't trust them at all.
All right, so you really
believe this.
>> Dude, it's real... this is
gonna happen.
>> Okay, all right.
>> For sure.
>> All right.
>> John.
>> So, basically, Russell and I
started talking, and he's, like,
"Who would you get rid of if you
could get rid of anybody
right now?"
Clearly, I said, John.
He's, like, "We can do that, I
think."
>> No.
It would be us four...
>> The next round, I know we can
get him.
But next round's gonna be a
four-four tie, 'cause Shambo's
gonna leave us in two seconds.
Taking her for granted.
You're telling me you really
agree with this?
>> This may be one of our only
shots to get rid of John.
>> Why?
>> Nothing's for sure, but it
just seems like we do have the
numbers.
>> You get rid of John and you
piss off Shambo, and she's
gonna go to the other side,
and then we're gonna have to
draw rocks.
>> I believe that Russell can
settle Shambo.
>> After leaving her out there
hanging the same way Galu did?
Exactly the same way?
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Erik, Kelly and Laura, voted
out at the last Tribal Council.
Jaison, you bypassed all the
food at the auction for one
thing, an advantage in the
immunity challenge, and look at
you tonight.
>> Thank God.
And some people might say you
only won it because you had the
advantage, but that doesn't
mean anything to me.
As long as I got a victory.
>> PROBST: Dave, do you think
that was the difference in the
challenge?
>> Honestly, it looked like it
was close, I wanted it real bad,
but in the end, my hand slipped
and his didn't, so...
>> PROBST: How concerned are
you that kind of physical
display could get you voted out
tonight?
>> It might have put a target
on my back, but I just wanted to
play my guts out and do my best.
>> PROBST: Shambo, after 30
days together, is it easier or
more difficult to get along
with people out here?
>> There has been so many ups
and downs within the last 30
days, but today was peaceful.
It wasn't about game play so
much, and it was genuine.
>> To me, today was strategic
only, completely strategic.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Shambo, did you say
"Wow"?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: That shocks you?
>> Yeah. I mean...
>> PROBST: Shambo, how is it
possible you are shocked to
learn that people were
scrambling to stay in the game?
>> My vote is being based on me
advancing in the game, number
one.
Number two, I do not want
somebody that did not warrant
getting a million dollars.
That's imperative to me in this
game.
>> PROBST: Dave, Shambo was
pretty clear.
Where do you think you sit in
her eyes?
>> I've done my best to be...
as honest and kind as I can with
Shambo.
You know, just be a good sport
about everything.
>> PROBST: John, Shambo wants
somebody who deserves to be
there.
Couldn't that be you?
>> You know, I don't think
that she thinks that I am
lacking in effort or a certain
worthiness of continuing on.
>> PROBST: Mick, last three
Tribal Councils, all blindsides.
You think somebody will be
surprised tonight?
>> You know, at this point, I
don't see how you would be
surprised.
I mean, if you look back here,
it looks like we're all getting
on planes tomorrow.
>> PROBST: Meaning everybody
brought their stuff.
>> Everybody brought their
stuff.
I mean, everyone has to come in
here ready to go home tonight.
>> Russell, you think whoever's
going home will be shocked?
>> I think they'll be surprised.
I do.
>> PROBST: Shambo, based on how
it's gone the last three times,
you think somebody's gonna
be shocked tonight?
>> I don't think they're gonna
be shocked at all.
>> PROBST: So you think they
know they're going.
>> I believe so.
>> PROBST: Dave, think it's
gonna be a shocking vote tonight
for somebody?
>> If this vote tonight goes
the way I'm expecting it to go,
I will be shocked.
>> PROBST: John, what's your
take on tonight's vote?
>> I think that of the two
potential names, you've asked
both of them questions, and
they both said they wouldn't be
shocked, so I think the answer
is no.
>> PROBST: All right, it's time
to get to the vote.
Jaison, you earned that
immunity.
I assume you're keeping it?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, you
cannot vote for Jaison.
Everybody else is fair game.
Let's see if the blindsides
continue.
It is time to vote.
Monica, you're up.
>> Dave, thanks for the
chickens.
They were great friends.
>> John, I'm voting for you
because it might get me closer
to a million bucks.
Sorry, pal.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay. Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Mick.
Dave.
One vote Mick, one vote Dave.
John.
One vote John.
Two votes John.
John.
That's three votes John, one
vote Mick, one vote Dave.
John.
That's four votes John, one vote
Mick, one vote Dave.
Tenth person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury...
John. That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
John, the tribe has spoken.
>> Pleasure, boys.
>> Bye, Johnny.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Well, I got to tell
you, based on how you've been
playing, I can't wait to see
what's gonna happen next.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
>> It's like a little kid sees
a snake, and the snake's, like,
"Hey, come play with me, I'm not
gonna bite you."
And the kid starts playing with
the snake, and the snake bites
him.
He's, like, "What happened?
You said you weren't gonna
bite me?"
He's, like, "I'm a snake.
That's what I do."
>> I think tonight's vote was
another decision made by Galu
that is a substandard decision.
They're scrambling, they're
doing anything they can to live
to see tomorrow.
The former Galu tribe is
intellectually outmatched.
I'm happy that I performed, you
know, well and made it into the
fourth quarter.
I think I had what it took to
go the distance, but it didn't
work out.