>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: Both tribes were
hammered hard by wind and rain.
>> I have never in my life been
this cold, had my hands this
destroyed, and my feet look so
miserable.
We're freezing.
>> PROBST: But with their huge
lead in numbers and rewards--
>> That looks so good.
>> PROBST: Galu still had plenty
of reason to celebrate.
>> After I finish this, I'll
take the whole team by myself.
>> PROBST: The only storm Galu
couldn't weather was Shambo.
>> Escaped chicken, escaped
chicken.
9-1-1.
>> Shambo is just a complete
Gilligan who just messes things
up all the time.
>> PROBST: On her second visit
to the Foa Foa tribe, it became
clear these were Shambo's real
friends.
>> I am really, really happy to
be over here with Foa Foa.
>> PROBST: Russell, on the
other hand, had no friends,
only targets.
>> Marisa threatened me, Betsy
threatened me-- each time
somebody threatened me, they're
going home.
>> PROBST: and when Liz
confronted Russell.
>> You are lying to me.
>> I'm telling you the truth.
Are you telling me I'm not
honest?
>> PROBST: She became next on
his hit list.
But after Liz's strong effort
in another loss-- Galu wins
immunity.
Russell put his vendetta
against her on the back burner
in order to jettison the
tribe's weakest member, Ashley.
>> It's because of me you're
going home.
I'm out here playing for
$1 million.
Never trust me.
>> PROBST: With only five Foa
Foa left, Liz needs a miracle
to save herself from Russell's
cruel intentions, assuming they
can all survive the conditions.
14 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(thunder crashing)
>> Are you shaking?
>> Yeah.
>> You're that cold?
I mean, I'm cold, too, but
geez.
>> okay, Mick's having a
seizure over here.
He's epileptic.
>> Since day ten, this is day
15 now, we're getting soaked at
night.
It's cold.
So, it's been pretty bad for
the last several nights.
I'll be honest, like there was
some envy last night when
Ashley went home.
There was a little tinge of
jealousy there.
I was like, "Oh, man," you know?
>> I really think we got
another two days of this, three
days, something.
>> I used to watch this cartoon
when I was growing up called
Captain Planet, and there was
always that one guy with the
ring, heart, and we always make
fun of him.
Like, "What is heart?"
Everybody else gets a real
element and you get heart."
And I really wish I had that
heart ring right now.
Because I'm tired, I'm really
hungry, and I'm sitting here
trying to battle what seems to
be a battle that fate just
doesn't want us to win.
What do you think?
Yeah.
>> It's not bad.
>> This is the man test.
>> If it takes seven days and
seven nights of rain for one
person to quit, I'll take it.
Hell, yeah, I'm having fun.
I'm out in the rain.
This is how I want it to be.
That sunny days we had for nine
days, I was like, "Man, this is
too pretty.
I'd take my family here."
I want to be somewhere where I
can't take my family, where
it's miserable.
>> (laughing)
>> What's wrong, man?
>> I'm so freaking cold right
now, it's ridiculous.
>> So silly.
>> I'm freezing!
>> Come on, man.
You can take this.
It's just a little water.
Man.
>> This isn't even right.
>> They're going to be soaking
wet, whether it stops raining
or not stops raining.
Tonight, they're going to be
wet, so this is really no big
deal.
As a matter of fact, this makes
me stronger.
(theme song playing)
(thunder rumbling)
(thunder crashing)
>> A what?
>> It's raining.
People are miserable.
Spirits are down.
And it could all be alleviated
had Russell gotten us that tarp.
But it's just the way the game
goes sometimes.
You know, one person is elected
to make decisions for the group.
Sometimes, it puts you in a
worse position than you would
have been if you were making
those decisions for yourself.
(thunder crashing)
>> Welcome to Samoa, brother.
Rain doesn't stop.
Russell's an animal.
>> Where is he?
>> Right there.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Russell was out working on
the fire while every single one
of us was huddled up trying to
stay warm, just trying to keep
sane, and he's out there just
busting his butt.
For me to see that, you know,
it's awesome to see him push
himself, but, also, like, you
know, it's great that you're
out there doing it, but at the
same time, it's like, no one
expects you to do that.
You know, it might have been to
a point where it was a bit
unnecessary and went a little
bit too far.
>> You know what?
There's no reason to be
sitting out here right now.
>> I'd rather be in the
shelter, but sometimes you have
to make some deposits in case
you need any withdrawals later
on.
You know, the chief thing
counter-balances to the
negative, so just trying to
keep the fire burning.
This is buying stock low.
Hopefully I'll be able to sell
high later.
>> Fire looks good though, huh?
>> I just got a chill.
Hold on.
>> Careful, careful, careful!
>> Are you okay?
>> Just hand me my jacket.
Just hand me my jacket.
>> Here you go.
>> Goodness!
Oh, that sucked.
That sucked.
>> Russell's definitely got
this, like, stubborn
determination to do everything.
But truth is, like, the
elements out here, like, it's
going to break you down.
He's just pushing himself too
hard and it's going to take its
toll, you know.
>> I can go back out there.
I just got to get my body
temperature back up.
(thunder crashing)
>> I probably look like some
crazy person, but basically,
this spot actually is a pretty
good cover.
I can kind of-- with my body
heat, kind of keep this corner
a little bit warm.
The shelter has so many gaps in
it, that when it rains this
hard, it just pours right
through.
I can't wear my clothes because
they're all soaking wet.
So I'm just doing the best I
can at just trying to stay
semi-warm and out of the rain
and...
Just trying to get through this.
>> It's wet.
They don't want to get out.
Where are they all from, New
York City?
"Got to stay dry.
Can't get my hair wet."
Man, this is crazy.
>> You never know, man, they
might also sucking each other's
thumbs because they're just a
bunch of babies.
That's why we lose the
challenges because they're lazy.
They give up.
They start walking, they start,
"I'm too tired."
Don't stop until you throw up,
you pass out, something.
If you don't throw up after
every frickin' challenge, you
didn't do your job.
That's how I think of it.
Now, it was freezing last night,
wet, cold.
It's time to do something about
it today, but they don't want
to.
They want to sit there and suck
on their thumbs.
So I don't know how to help
them.
I don't think it's going to
stop raining.
(thunder rumbling)
>> (groans)
I had been in my hole for, you
know, almost 26 straight hours
of rain, and I was laying in
the hole and I was, like, "Okay,
I give in. We give in.
We understand your greatness.
We understand your power.
And if you are kind to us, I
promise we will speak of your
mercy."
And less than 12 hours later, I
wake up from my hole, and not
only is it blue skies, but the
most beautiful rainbow you have
ever seen.
It's as if Samoa said, "That's
all I wanted to hear, Erik.
Just know I'm the man, you're
not.
Now that we got that clear,
enjoy yourself for the next 24
days."
I'm so happy.
>> That's a nice sign, isn't it?
>> That's a real nice sign.
I don't think they have a
rainbow on Foa Foa's side of
the island.
>> A rainbow.
That is really, really nice to
wake up to.
I mean, getting a ray of
sunshine today was like-- you
talk about lifting spirits.
You know, winning challenges
and rewards-- nothing beat this
morning.
>> Look at that!
>> I feel like we just got off
of Noah's Ark.
>> There actually is a sky out
there other than just clouds.
Can you believe it?
Look!
There's blue sky out there!
I think going through a storm
like this, I think it
definitely brings the tribe
together, 'cause we weathered
it all together.
Now that we're out, we know
we've got a task at hand, and
we're stronger than ever.
I mean, we really are.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Galu, getting your first look at
the new Foa Foa tribe.
Ashley voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
All right, you guys ready to
get to today's challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, one person from each
tribe will be strapped into a
large sphere.
That person will then guide two
blindfolded tribe mates as they
push the sphere through a long
course to a table maze.
The person inside the sphere
will then guide the rest of
their blindfolded tribe mates
as they navigate a ball through
a table maze to a finish hole.
First tribe to get it right
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Pizza!
Hot, piping pizza.
You guys have been enduring a
lot of rain.
A nice, hot pizza will go down
really good, right?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: There's one twist--
win or lose, both tribes going
to Tribal Council.
Both tribes will vote somebody
out tonight.
You'll enjoy the pizza tonight
when the winning tribe sits in
on the losing tribe's Tribal
Council.
>> Oh, yeah, yeah.
>> PROBST: So, not only will
you see what is going on within
the tribe, you will do it by
enjoying pizza in front of them.
All right, Galu, you have four
extra members, sitting four
people out.
Who's going to sit out this
challenge?
>> You know, I feel weaker as
the days go on, but I'm the
leader.
I got to go forward.
I can't look back.
And I'm playing the game.
Monica, Kelly, Shambo, Dave.
>> PROBST: All right, you four
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
For Foa Foa, navigating in the
ball is Liz; pushing, Russell
and Jaison.
For Galu, it's Laura in the
ball; Russell and Erik doing
the pushing.
Here we go!
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Straight, straight.
>> Go, go, go.
Keep going. Keep going.
>> PROBST: Galu off to a good
start.
>> Okay, left, left, left.
To your left!
Good, good, good.
Keep going.
They're behind us.
>> Straight, straight, straight.
>> Right, right, go!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa pushing
their ball right into Erik.
They're on top of Erik.
>> Straight, straight.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa trying to
sneak around the right.
Liz does it.
Foa Foa now in the lead.
>> To your right, to your right.
To your right.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa now off
course.
Galu now back in the lead.
>> Forward, forward, forward!
>> PROBST: Laura has Russell and
Erik doing a great job.
>> Forward, forward, forward.
>> PROBST: Galu right into the
tree.
Foa Foa now trying to go around
them again.
>> Hold it. Now forward.
>> PROBST: They are side by
side.
>> Go, straight ahead.
Straight ahead.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa now in the
lead.
>> Russell, push!
Under the side, Russell!
>> This way?
>> Russell, no, no.
Erik, stop.
Hold on, hold on.
>> One short turn.
Perfect, now bring it home.
We're almost there.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa very close.
Galu stuck.
>> Come on, Galu!
Laura, direct them, Laura, we
can't hear you!
>> Russell, go, go, push, push.
>> PROBST: Russell is exhausted.
>> Russell, push.
>> I'm pushing.
>> There you go, one more.
Okay, now--
>> PROBST: Foa Foa.
You're good.
Now you've got to orient Liz so
she can see.
>> Upright.
>> Yeah, pull up. Pull up
>> Towards me!
Russ, Russ, harder, push harder.
>> PROBST: Russell, Erik, and
Laura still struggling to get to
the finish.
>> Okay, now, get into your
positions.
>> PROBST: Liz, happy where she
is.
>> Go, go, go.
Keep going, come on, Russ!
>> PROBST: Galu getting very
close now.
Galu has their ball in the
right spot.
Erik gets crushed in the end.
>> Get to your spots!
>> Mick, go...
>> PROBST: Galu put Laura in
great position.
No extra orientation needed.
>> Left, left, left, to your
left, left, left, left.
Left, Russ, left.
>> Hold on. Stop.
>> Russell.
>> Russell!
>> PROBST: Laura trying to get
Russell on the course.
He is exhausted.
>> Don't fall.
>> PROBST: He has no idea where
he's at right now.
>> Lean down, lean down.
Go to your right, go to your
right, go to your right.
>> Grab the handle!
>> Jaison, push your hands down.
>> Straight down, Mick, straight
down.
>> Straight down.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa now has a bit
of a lead on the table maze.
>> Brett, down.
Brett down!
John, up.
The ball is right in the middle.
>> Don't move. Don't move.
Don't move!
Stop moving. Stop moving!
>> Russell, get off the table.
>> Russell.
>> PROBST: Whoa?
Russell, you with me?
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Everybody hold up.
Medical!
Hold where you are.
Everybody, hold where you are.
>> Hold it, hold it, Galu.
Hold it right here.
>> PROBST: Hold right where you
are.
>> Yeah, yeah.
I'm good.
>> PROBST: He-- he was out.
He was definitely out.
>> Yeah, I saw that.
>> Russell, can you sit down
for a moment?
>> PROBST: Yeah, yeah, take
over.
>> Russell, sit down.
Russell.
Lie him down.
Can you get the last pack?
>> Russell, can you hear me?
>> Come on, Russ.
>> Russ?
Russ, talk to me.
Can someone get me that life
pack?
>> Danielle, can you get the
life pack?
>> Russell passed out during
the challenge.
I mean, I saw him stumbling
around, staggering.
And I figured it was because he
was blindfolded.
I couldn't figure out exactly
what was going on.
I should have guessed he passed
out.
>> Russell, you can hear me?
>> I'm good.
Let's go.
>> PROBST: You passed out for a
minute.
You weren't with us for a
second.
Just relax and let them do what
they're doing.
Everybody, you can take off
your blindfolds.
>> Your blood pressure is really
low too, Russ.
I'm just going to have a listen
to your heart there.
>> I'm cool.
I mean, I was a little winded
from pushing the ball, but I'm
good.
>> You just need to relax just
for a little while, okay?
>> PROBST: Ramona, what's the
update?
>> His blood pressure is even
lower than Mike's was.
If we stood him up now, he'd
just black out and collapse
again.
>> PROBST: All right, here's--
here's what's going to happen.
I'm going to make a call right
now, which is this challenge is
over.
Neither tribe wins reward.
Both tribes will go to Tribal
Council tonight.
Both tribes will vote somebody
out tonight.
You're going to both head back
to camp.
We'll stay here and monitor
Russell.
If he's able to return to the
game, you'll see him at Tribal
Council.
Foa Foa, grab your stuff, head
on out.
>> Feel better, Russell.
>> PROBST: All right, Galu,
grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> We'll be waiting for you,
Russ. Get better.
>> We'll see you back there.
>> PROBST: Either way, we'll
see you tonight at Tribal
Council.
>> Hang tight, chief.
>> If he comes back, I will be
shocked.
I'll be happy, but I'll be
>> You think Russ is okay?
>> No.
>> You don't think he's coming
back?
>> No.
But I'm not a doctor, I don't
know.
>> Everyone's concerned about
Russell.
For Russell to go down the way
he did today, it shows you how
tough this game is.
No one has any experience with
this level of dehydration.
the level of malnutrition that
we go through.
And a guy like Russell gives
you everything he's got and
more every single time, and
then he comes back and he's a
workhorse.
And his body failed him today.
And it's so unfortunate.
>> I'm about to make a break
for the shelter.
(thunder crashing)
>> I'm so sick of the rain.
>> Yeah, me, too.
>> Our leader's not here.
And that's a big hit to take.
(thunder crashing)
It's kind of surreal.
We're kind of just not really
knowing really what to do.
We're used to, we're used to
rallying and saying, "Okay,
give us our game plan."
(thunder crashing)
Uh, but you can't let these
emotional things distract you
too much out of the game.
You have to keep your focus.
Uh, we still are playing
the game.
We're still thinking about the
next person that, that's
going to go.
But I know my heart is really
heavy for Russell.
I just hope that he's okay.
(sighs)
>> All right, we'll try and sit
him up.
>> PROBST: Sounds good.
>> All right.
>> I just want you to sit up
from where you are.
Just to there.
Any head spins there?
>> A little light-headed.
>> A little light-headed? Okay.
Stay exactly like that.
I'm gonna take your blood
pressure again straight away
and see what change we got.
(device beeping)
Russ, are you okay?
Russ?
Russ? Russ? Just lie down.
Come on, Russ. Russ?
Russ? Russ, are you with us?
Lie down. Russ?
>> Russell.
>> Russ, talk to me.
Russ, talk to me.
Russell, Russell,
wake up, mate.
Wake up.
You there? Mm-hmm?
Do you remember what
just happened?
>> Huh?
>> His heart rate was 97 when we
sat him up, and now it's 68.
Okay?
>> PROBST: And it dropped
like that.
>> It dropped really
quickly.
>> PROBST: Just so you're clear
on what's happening is,
is we're going to have to pull
you out of the game.
There's no question to all of
us watching, brother, that, that
you are not okay.
>> Come on, come on.
>> PROBST: Russell, we've hung
in there as long as we can.
You are not doing well.
I just watched your, your heart
rate plummet.
>> My family depends on me to
be the strong one.
Is this how you want this
to end?
>> PROBST: No, no.
It's frustrating to be pulled
out of a game you wanted to be
a part of for so long.
You were in great shape.
You were the leader of a tribe
that was dominating.
You heard no sign that you were
going home any time soon.
You pushed and pushed and
pushed your body until your
body said, "Enough."
There's nothing about that that
is a quitter, nothing.
>> But I'm just dehydrated.
I'm not...
>> PROBST: But you're not
recovering fast enough.
You need help, and if you
don't, you're gonna be worse.
Russell, I watched you black
out in front of me two times.
There's no way you could have
stayed in this game.
I'm gonna leave you alone
and stop talking.
(Russell sobbing softly)
>> I feel bittersweet because
we were close to winning, and
then big Russell had his
medical accident.
But when Jeff said that we
still had to go to Tribal
Council, regardless of who won
the challenge, it was
surprising, and, you know, a
little upsetting because none
of us want to go back there.
We were just there.
>> I'm packing my bags.
>> I'm for sure packing mine.
>> I have a fair sense of
what's going on.
There's five of us.
We're, again, one big family.
Natalie and I, we both looked
at each other and said it's
gonna be one of us.
And it will be.
I mean, at this point, we need
to continue to win, and it
doesn't make sense to vote out
one of the guys.
My gut tells me maybe I'll
stick around because I'm just
competitively stronger, but my
fate and Natalie's fate rest in
the three guys in our tribe.
>> Your vote's very simple
tonight.
>> What is it?
>> It's Liz. And then, uh...
>> She and I talked about it.
>> And I'm... I'm trying my
best right now.
Because you know you and Liz
are the two names, of course.
>> For sure. We knew that.
>> So, uh, 'cause I'm putting
Liz, you putting Liz.
I know I can talk Mick into
putting Liz no matter what.
>> I mean, no, she and I
already talked.
We know that it's pretty simple;
I'm voting for her, and she's
voting for me.
>> Yeah.
>> How what?
>> I'd like to stay if it's
possible.
>> Every time that we come
close to something good, it
kind of gets taken away.
So, winning today would have
been our revenge, you know.
They would have had to watch us
eat and, you know, understand
how we felt.
And we were winning.
I think what's the most
disheartening is not
necessarily the losses, but
just the random things that
keep happening every time you
think you have something good
to go bad.
And, you know, I really hope
Russell's okay.
I mean, that, clearly, is the
primary concern.
I agree with the decision to
cancel the challenge and all
that stuff.
It just, uh, it just kind of
sucks that when you finally
feel like you're getting in a
groove and going someplace,
it's like, "No, sorry."
>> Do you think we would have
won that?
>> I think we were winning
by a lot.
I'm just wondering, with all
the stars seeming to be aligned
against us, how many of us
actually have a shot at getting
real far, you know?
>> Well, I mean, look at...
>> This tribe could be done by
day 21, the rate we're going.
>> I think it could be done.
I think it can be done.
They'll have people flip
over there.
>> I have a feeling that
Shambo's going to be gunning
for me, and so I want to be
sure that you have my back.
>> Hold on, hold on.
Shh! Shh! Don't talk!
Don't talk!
They were all over, and
they're probably up here,
my crabs.
>> Yeah.
>> If we were going to Tribal
Council, right now, Shambo is
going, 100%.
>> Here's a medium.
>> From day one, she's never
really jelled with the tribe,
and she's been over to the
other tribe.
None of us have.
And so when we merge, she could
very easily flop sides.
>> So what's, what's the
skinny, baby?
We're voting somebody off
tonight.
>> I don't know, honestly, who
should go home.
I don't know.
I didn't, like, I honestly
didn't think we'd come to like
a second Tribal.
I don't know.
>> Ever?
>> I mean, I thought we would
go to the merge first.
>> See, I'm just asking you guys
to not write my name down today.
>> Mm-hmm.
I mean, I started the fire the
first eight days we were here.
>> Yeah.
>> Chief and I collected 100% of
the firewood the first eight
days we were here.
I have been a good competitor,
an honest competitor,
a fair competitor.
I have not lied to anyone in
this game.
>> That's fine, but despite the
fact, my name got written
down twice.
The only person here who wrote
it down last Tribal was you.
>> So, you're writing my name
down tonight?
>> I don't know if I'm writing
your name down.
I can't guarantee you anything.
>> Who-who made fire for you the
first eight days you were
here, Monica?
Who kept you warm and dry
and safe?
>> Who didn't write my
name down?
Everyone else in this tribe
except for you!
The number one reason for
voting off Shambo, for me, is
the fact she wrote my name down
last time.
And you got to take your enemy
out the minute you can, and
right now seems like an
opportune moment.
>> As far as the weak girls go,
who's the weakest girl?
>> Monica.
>> Totally!
>> Right?
Bar none.
>> Yeah.
>> And I'm sorry, as much as
people like to talk Shambo, we
would not have won the fishing
gear in that first immunity and
started this whole ball rolling
without her.
And she poses no threat
to anybody.
>> Exactly, exactly.
>> No threat.
>> Exactly. None.
>> Post-merge, she does not
have the power, the
manipulative power that a
Laura-Monica tag team or a
Laura or a Monica sole have.
>> Voting Shambo off doesn't do
anything beneficial for
any of us.
Monica needs to go for
several reasons:
one, Monica and Laura have this
mother-daughter/sister-sister
relationship.
Post-merge, that's gonna
be dangerous.
One of the two of them needs to
go while we still have a
chance to get 'em.
Laura will be severely weakened
without Monica.
And Monica, I think, is the
clear move because Monica
doesn't help us win challenges
at all.
Is there a better move than
than that?
'Cause I can't think of any.
>> This is not a bad plan.
>> So it's me, you, Brett, Dave
makes four.
Either Coach or Shambo come
back, we have numbers;
game over.
No one flips.
>> Who else out here hasn't
lied but me?
No one.
Don't vote me off tonight.
>> Yeah, I know that about you,
Sham, but I know... I know that
your effort speaks for itself.
>> Obviously, it doesn't if
you're not telling me you're
not writing my name down.
>> Just 'cause I'm not telling
you I'm not writing your name
down doesn't mean I'm not
writing your name down.
>> Okay.
>> Shambo is on a very
need-to-know basis.
Us four guys-- Dave, Brett, and
John-- we're pretty good about
keeping the plan within the
four of us.
We're not gonna be telling
her anything more than what she
needs to know.
>> So where you at tonight?
>> What are your thoughts?
>> Erik, if you were Shambo,
who would you vote for tonight?
>> Yeah.
>> Not me.
>> Not you.
>> If I was Shambo, I would
probably stay consistent.
>> Who?
>> Consistent.
I'd stay consistent.
>> Meaning who you voted for
last time is probably your
best bet?
>> You would stay consistent.
>> If I was Shambo.
>> What if you were John?
>> Um, I would follow
the leader; as in Shambo's
the leader.
>> Really?
And if you were Erik, who would
you vote for?
>> I'd vote for Monica.
>> Really?
>> Who are you voting
for, Shambo?
Do you get what this is
about yet?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Brett's down with it.
>> He is? Okay, good.
>> Dave's down with it.
And that's a wrap.
>> Okay, cool.
>> Sham, you got to lock it up.
>> Lock it up.
>> No worries.
If that's what you want from
me, that's what you've got.
>> And don't even-- Hounding at
this is not locking it up.
>> PROBST: Well, this is a
first-- 13 people at Tribal
Council.
All right, let me give
everybody an update.
Russell was pulled from the
game.
After you guys left, the
doctors continued to monitor
his blood pressure, blood
pressure was steady.
Two, three minutes in, out of
nowhere, his heart rate dropped
like that.
He blacked out again, went down
on his back.
At that point, there was no
question he needed to be pulled
from the game.
It was the scariest moment I've
ever had on this show.
19 seasons, I have never been
more afraid in my life of how
bad things were.
Russell was in terrible shape.
So, the update now is that he
is in very good hands, being
monitored, doing fine.
There was no way he could have
come back into the game.
Shambo, what's your reaction to
hearing that he's no longer in
the game?
>> I feel really sad that
that's how he went out, because
you see this guy with this
amazing heart and spirit bigger
than life.
So, I mean, it's-- it's
terribly sad.
>> PROBST: Russell, on one
hand, it's a break for Foa Foa.
>> Yeah, he was definitely the
strongest on their tribe.
But I just don't like the fact
that that's how he went out,
you know?
I mean, if I was going to beat
him, I don't want to beat him
like that.
>> PROBST: Dave, what does it
say about this game, when
you're watching not only
somebody you're on a tribe
with, and you're also competing
against, but just another human
being, going through this
crisis?
>> Well, you know, it's
definitely an eye-opener for me.
I mean, you get out here and
it's like a whole different
level that I did not expect.
It's been raining for days.
We haven't been dry for more
than an hour.
It's pretty intense, easily the
hardest thing I've ever done,
and I've done a couple of hard
things in my life.
>> PROBST: Erik, this has been
15 of the toughest days I've
seen any group go through.
>> I spent 22 hours in the
bottom of a tree trunk, and
with 22 hours, the inability to
sleep, you prayed about
anything that you could think
of.
>> PROBST: Are you literally
praying?
>> I prayed to God.
I prayed to Samoa.
(thunder)
I prayed to... I don't know.
I feel like I'm in solitary
confinement for a crime I
didn't commit, and that is not
anything that was advertised.
>> PROBST: Shambo, what is it
that keeps you from saying,
"I'm going to quit?"
>> I'm the 45-year-old lady
here that-- that will not quit.
(thunder)
And I have been, like Erik,
shivering and praying-- "Dear,
God, this is Shannon from
Renton.
Please, please, please let the
sun shine."
>> PROBST: And as we sit here,
it is starting to pour once
again.
>> Yup.
>> You know, it's not just the
misery that the rain brings,
but it's the constant fear, the
constant torture that it's not
going to stop.
And every minute, you're
terrified.
>> PROBST: Dave, first time
we've had everybody here
together.
What's the status of the game
right now?
>> Right now, it appears, you
know, just based on numbers,
that Galu is ahead.
And I don't know how their
spirits are, but they haven't
had quite the sustenance that
we have.
And I know that our spirits, in
spite of the rain, are pretty
high.
>> PROBST: Russell, Dave thinks
Galu is winning right now.
Not so good over here at Foa
Foa?
>> Attitude at Foa Foa is-- is
fine.
And I think they're going to be
shocked in the next couple of
challenges because we can come
back.
We can even up them numbers,
and then it will be a different
story then.
>> PROBST: Mick, does today's
challenge, even though we
didn't finish it, feel like a
moral victory for Foa Foa?
>> Yeah, absolutely.
I mean, we have to take this as
a win.
We feel like, at that point, we
were ahead, and so we'd like to
think that it would have played
out and we would have won.
>> PROBST: Erik, it's got to
concern you a little bit.
This group of five believes
they won today's challenge.
>> well, they had a big win a
few challenges ago.
We came back and we brought it
again.
And now today, they got a tie,
and that's supposed to make us
nervous about a momentum shift?
I don't think so.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the topic of the vote.
Due to the unprecedented nature
of today's events, in which,
for the first time ever, we did
not complete a challenge, there
will be no Tribal Council vote
tonight.
Nobody going home.
Galu, you're not voting anybody
out.
Foa Foa, you will not vote
anybody out.
I'm seeing a lot of mixed
reactions.
Some happy people.
And some jaws that are hitting
the floor.
Erik, is this good news?
>> We lost a guy today.
So, whether we're voting or not
voting, we're down already.
So let's stop the bleeding at
one.
>> PROBST: Russell, you guys
would be down to four if you
voted someone out tonight.
>> Yeah, I think it's the best
news I heard all day, because
right now, us five, we're the
strongest that we've ever been
this whole game.
So now, if they beat us fair and
square, then we'll send
somebody home.
But I really believe that the
table's about to turn and I'll
give 110% that it does, so I'm
going to go all out.
>> PROBST: Erik, with every
comment from Foa Foa about
"bring it," you're getting more
and more forward.
>> Let's line it up and let's
do a challenge right now.
You know, because that's what
Russell would do.
He'd be saying, "Are you
kidding me?
There's five of them over there
and there are eight of us over
here."
I don't know if there's emotion
in me that comes up, but every
bead of sweat that he put into
everything he ever did, we're
bringing that to you.
We will bring that every day,
every challenge.
>> We welcome it.
>> PROBST: Well, it is clear
that the events of today have
only intensified the rivalry
between these two tribes.
Foa Foa believes they've got a
moral victory today, and now
they can turn this game around.
And Galu believing, "Even
though we lost Russell, his
spirit is still with us and we
will continue to dominate this
game."
We're in store for a great
finish.
There is one order of
business-- Galu, you are now
without a leader.
Somebody come grab this.
When you get back to camp,
assign a new leader.
That concludes things for
tonight.
Foa Foa, grab your torches head
back to camp.
Galu, grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> Being taken out of the game
for medical reasons is the worst
thing I've ever felt in my life.
>> One, two, three, lift.
>> I played every minute to win
this game.
And to have my body fail me is
utterly demoralizing.
But even though it pains me to
not be in it, to do it and fail
is better than to never try.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor: At Galu, the guys
make Shambo one of their own.
>> Only strategic drawback is
that Shambo is so dim that she
could screw up our plan.
>> PROBST: And a Russell seed
gets planted in the other tribe.
>> What I have to do now is
work my Houdini magic.
>> What are we going to do?
Go to the final two, the two of
us?
>> Final two.
>> I'm really ashamed that, you
know, I'm not in the game
anymore.
And I'm angry, because I'm a
fighter.
But at the same time, I have to
be realistic because I have to
get well, because I have an
even bigger job to do, one that
I love, one they cherish every
day.
And that's being a husband to
my wife a father to my child.