>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor: after eight days, the
yellow tribe Foa Foa, had been
to the first three Tribal
Councils.
>> I just want to survive to
another day.
I'm tired.
I'm hungry.
>> PROBST: Tensions were high.
Nerves were frayed, and the
only person who wasn't
miserable was Russell.
>> When people fight I love
that.
Now, I try to start the fight.
>> PROBST: He now has the
hidden immunity idol...
>> Boo-yah.
>> PROBST: And a diabolical
plan.
>> They can be my little
puppets.
When I'm finished with them,
just throw them in the trash.
>> PROBST: Over at Galu, Shambo
had problems fitting in with the
rest of her tribe.
>> Galu is like they're in high
school.
The young people want to lay on
the beach and gossip.
>> PROBST: She broke their
fishing gear.
>> It's in the swamp.
There's nothing I can do.
>> PROBST: And lost one of
their chickens.
>> Shambo is a complete
Gilligan who messes just things
up all the time.
>> PROBST: Shambo's best
friends are on Foa Foa who she
bonded with when she visited
their camp.
>> There was a huge
appreciation for Shambo.
>> PROBST: One, two, three,
four, five.
Foa Foa wins their first
immunity challenge!
When Galu finally lost an
immunity challenge, Russell
wanted to take out Monica.
But most of the others wanted
Yasmin to go home.
>> She does the least out of
everyone here.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Russell reluctantly sided with
the majority.
>> I'm sorry.
>> PROBST: Yasmin was gone.
And by voting for Monica,
Shambo further alienated
herself from her tribe.
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Everybody go left behind me.
And then we'll be in front of
the fire in a minute.
Well, we just got back from our
first Tribal Council, and
Yasmin got voted out.
I didn't expect it, not by a
long shot.
>> Do we have any flame there,
Shambo?
>> I haven't gotten to the
pot yet.
I'm doing that right now,
darling.
We do.
>> Okay, perfect.
>> Let me get this pot out of
the way so nobody gets hurt
on it.
I'm a little disparaged about
the fact that every single
person on our team was in
alignment, with the exception
of myself.
I'm absolutely exhausted and
hopefully I'll get some good
sleep tonight and pick up the
pieces tomorrow.
So it's like...
Whereas we can just sit here
and just chill and not do
anything about it.
>> So Tribal was pretty crazy.
Now in retrospect I realize
that Shambo is the only person
here who voted against me, so
that kind of hangs over my head
a little bit, and so I
definitely want to continue and
take Sham off.
She's my next choice.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> This ocean is a real bitch.
When, you know, you try to go
out there, it hits with you
massive tides and waves that
suck you and pull you and send
you all over the place.
I've never seen an object,
inanimate, or animate, that was
as angry and fickle as this
ocean.
>> The ocean is not playing
around right now.
>> Oh, my God.
Like, is there a hurricane out
there?
>> It's day 12, and we finally
came off a win.
We're still excited.
The sun's shining.
The ocean's been crazy.
>> What if our flag washed away.
>> But seems like maybe it's a
bright day for Foa Foa.
>> Tree mail.
>> You guys ready?
>> Ready.
>> "The ocean's deep provide
many a treat.
Some pay a fortune for what you
will eat.
If you keep it all down inside
your tummy, you just may win
something yummy."
>> No!
>> Oh, no, it's a food
challenge.
>> Oh, no!
We're going to have to eat
gross, like, stuff from the
ocean.
>> Oh, my God!
>> What do you mean gross
stuff, like fish?
>> Just do it.
>> No!
>> It's gonna be nasty stuff.
>> No it will be like
Samoan rat.
>> The trick is, you can't
throw it up.
You have to keep it down.
You cannot puke.
>> I know.
>> I'm actually really excited
about our reward challenge.
I'm a pretty experimental eater.
I'll try everything once.
So hopefully this comes to my
advantage and hopefully I am
one of the stronger people on
my tribe today.
>> Why?
>> You said it was going to be
a hard time for you, didn't you?
>> No, I said I'd eat it.
I'd just be grossed out.
>> I was about to say, "You done
with this?
You trying to put her on some
kind of chopping block?
You want me to just watch her,
just watch her individual
eating challenge?
>> Right.
I know, she's always spreading
little...
>> Yeah, she's trying to spread
little seeds to grow in
people's heads.
She should just shut up
about it.
Liz could be dangerous for me
if she's able to manipulate
other to go her way instead of
my way.
So as soon as I see somebody
playing that mind game on other
people, they're a huge threat
because that's what this game
is all about is mind games, and
I've gotta be the only mind
game player here.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Foa Foa, getting your first
look at the new Galu tribe.
Yasmin voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yup.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: If there is one
thing I am sure of, it is
this-- you are all hungry.
>> Yes.
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: The good news is,
today you will eat.
I'll spin the wheel.
One member of each tribe will
roll a ball.
The ball will land on different
ingredients.
I will then blend those
ingredients to make a Samoa
smoothie.
And you will then gulp it down.
Each time you get it down, you
score a point for your tribe.
It's not a race.
If you get it down, you score a
point.
First tribe to five wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: If you can get the
bad stuff down you get the good
stuff.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Survivor barbecue.
All you have to do is get the
smoothie down.
>> Drink it.
I don't care what it tastes
like.
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will send one of
its members over to the losing
tribe for a little spy
expedition, which means that
person will miss out on the
reward.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: All right, Galu,
you're sitting out three people
this challenge.
Keep in mind, you cannot sit
out the same people in
back-to-back challenges.
Who's it going to be Russell?
>> It's going to be Kelly,
Laura, and John.
>> PROBST: Kelly, Laura, John,
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else take a spot on
your benches, and we will get
started.
All right, first two.
Shambo for Galu taking on
Jaison.
What ingredients will we have
in our first smoothie?
Oh, I like this one.
I like it.
We have giant clam and we have
Jeff's choice.
>> Sweet.
>> PROBST: First the giant clam.
>> Yummy.
>> PROBST: That looks pretty
good.
Jeff's choice means I get to
add whatever I'd like.
And the flies seem to really
like the octopus.
>> All right!
>> PROBST: Let's see what else
we can have.
How about a sea snail or two.
>> Really?
>> PROBST: And I'm gonna
give you a little noni juice.
>> You got this, Jaison, no
worries.
>> Think of the steaks.
>> PROBST: Add a little
garnish, fresh seaweed.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Cheers.
>> Cheers.
>> Get it, Sham.
>> Don't chew, just swallow.
>> Come on, Jaison.
>> PROBST: Shambo not messing
around at all.
>> Okay, take it downtown.
>> You got it, girl.
>> Yeah, that's the stuff.
>> Good job, Jaison.
(cheers and applause)
>> PROBST: Shambo, you're done.
Have a seat.
>> Good job, Sham.
Good job, baby.
>> PROBST: Oh, that one's look
tough.
>> You got it, Jaison.
You got it, you got it.
>> PROBST: It's his last gulp.
>> It's coming up!
>> Stay with it, Jaison, you
got it.
>> PROBST: And he keeps it down.
Jaison scores for Foa Foa.
We are tied one-one.
Next two.
We have Russell taking on
Russell.
>> The battle of the Russells!
>> PROBST: Wow, you landed on
the same one.
It's a jellyfish special.
Let me just get in here and get
some good helping of jellyfish.
>> All right!
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yummy!
>> PROBST: I think I'm going to
go milk.
>> Milk. Oh, my God!
Oh, milk!
>> I don't even drink milk by
itself.
>> PROBST: Well, you're going to
really enjoy this.
Bon appétit, gentlemen.
Bottoms up.
>> Cheers, fellows.
>> Slow and steady, Russell.
>> PROBST: Great way to start
day 12 on Survivor: Samoa.
>> Nasty.
(Russell groans)
(Galu cheers)
>> That's it.
>> PROBST: Russell says no
problem.
>> All right, Russell, take
your time, baby, take your time.
>> PROBST: Oh, Russell-- other
Russell spitting it up.
>> Come on, Russ!
Think about the steak.
>> Think about the steaks,
brother.
Think about those steak and
and sausages.
>> Steaks for dinner.
Get it, get it, get it, get it!
>> PROBST: Not messing around
now; that's what you call a
survivor right there.
(Foa Foa cheering)
Nice job.
(applause)
After two rounds, we are tied,
2-2.
Very impressive.
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Next round.
Brett for Galu taking on Mick
for Foa Foa.
Giant clam with sea cucumber.
A little sea cucumber.
Let's do milk.
>> Mmm.
>> Does the body good.
(blender whirring)
>> PROBST: Sea cucumber and
giant clams, courtesy of
Survivor.
Enjoy, gentlemen.
>> Yeah, Mick!
All right, Mick!
>> You got it.
>> Free food, Mick.
>> Steak! Steak!
>> PROBST: This is a chunky
shake.
Nothing smooth about this
smoothie.
>> Come on, Brett, you can do
it, buddy.
>> God, Yeah!
>> PROBST: Mick is not messing
around.
(applause, cheering)
Empty.
Mick scores for Foa Foa.
Take a seat.
>> All right!
>> Awesome!
>> Don't puke, baby.
>> PROBST: Brett's getting
every last drop.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Licking the glass.
He's a freak.
>> I think that's about good.
>> PROBST: Nice job.
We're tied 3-3.
Next two.
It's Monica for Galu and Liz
for Foa Foa.
Both balls land on sea urchin.
Since both balls landed on it,
I think we'll just give the
full deal.
>> There's no worries.
>> Yeah, you got it, Liz.
It's a protein shake.
(blender whirring)
>> PROBST: Wow, it's like a
chocolate shake.
(Monica laughs)
>> PROBST: A little sea noodle
for a garnish.
Cheers.
>> All right, Liz, you got it.
>> Good job, Liz, you can do it.
>> PROBST: Monica takes that sea
noodle out.
Don't lose any of that.
Liz plugging her nose.
>> All right, Liz, you got it.
>> PROBST: Monica does not waste
anything time.
She's just trying to throw this
down.
>> You're doing good, Liz, yeah.
>> PROBST: Liz trying to avoid
that rancid smell.
Monica shoving the sea noodle
down.
That is impressive.
The girl can eat.
>> Slow and steady, Liz.
>> PROBST: Monica, show me that
empty mouth.
Nice job.
Monica scores for Galu.
(cheers and applause )
>> PROBST: Liz very close for
Foa Foa.
>> Good job, girl.
>> PROBST: Nice job, Liz.
We are still tied, 4-4.
Ashley for Foa Foa.
Dave for Galu.
You both get your drink down,
we will go to a tie-breaker.
Sea slug guts.
Maybe the worst thing out here.
>> Awesome.
That's what I want.
>> PROBST: The guts of a sea
slug.
Let's go water with this one so
we can really see what it looks
like.
>> Oh, great!
I'll give it a little bit of a
blend but not a lot.
(blender whirring)
>> You think those are kidneys
or livers or what?
>> I don't really want to know.
>> PROBST: Chunks for Ashley;
a few more chunks for Dave.
Here we go.
Sea slug guts, compliments of
the house.
(glasses clink)
>> You got this Ashley, no
worries.
>> PROBST: You wanted to be on
Survivor.
Welcome to the game.
>> Whoo!
(Dave sputtering)
>> Good job, Ash.
>> (groaning): Ugh!
(Dave retching, shudders)
>> Take your time.
>> PROBST: Ashley trying to
block out Dave's near-vomit
sounds.
Dave gets it down for Galu.
(applause)
Ashley gotta get this down to
force a tie-breaker.
>> No worries.
You got this.
>> Oh... don't puke.
It looks like she already
vomited in the glass, and then
she's got to drink the vomit.
>> Oh, God, there she goes.
>> Suck it up.
(all groaning with disgust)
>> PROBST: Ashley needs to get
this down.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: You're going to have
to swallow and chug.
>> (groaning): Oh!
>> Can't do it.
>> Aw...
>> PROBST: Ashley can't finish
for Foa Foa.
Galu wins reward!
(Galu cheering)
>> Yeah!
(cheering and laughter)
>> I'm going to puke again.
Sorry, guys.
>> It's all right.
>> Oh.
>> God.
>> PROBST: Galu,
congratulations. Nice job.
>> Thank you.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: First order of
business-- Russell, you're
sending one person from your
tribe over to Foa Foa's camp.
They will stay with them until
the next immunity challenge.
So whoever you choose is going
to miss out on this reward.
>> I'm going to send my girl
Shambo again.
>> Excuse me?
>> We need more info, babe.
>> I don't think that's very
fair since I've already been.
>> I mean, what do you...
What do you want me to do?
>> Can you spread the love for
me?
>> PROBST: Russell has made his
decision.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: All right, Shambo.
This is for you to open in
private.
Join Foa Foa on their bench.
>> Hi, kids.
>> Had to pay for that chicken.
>> PROBST: Galu, your reward.
Come get it.
Head back to camp.
Have a great afternoon.
>> Yay!
>> I'm so bummed out.
I'm pissed.
Having Russell say that I had to
come over to Foa Foa.
It's not coming to Foa Foa.
It's missing out on the protein
that my body so badly needs
right now.
I feel like I got hit by a train
today.
>> I don't even care about
reward.
>> Yeah.
>> You guys are pissed.
Imagine how I feel.
>> We're happy to have you, but
I totally understand how you
feel.
>> I'm happy to be here with
you guys.
You guys are all sweethearts.
There's no hidden agenda.
What you see is what you get.
>> Sorry we don't have steaks
for you.
>> Yeah.
>> It's all good, man.
I don't need a damn steak.
I'll-I'll take a group hug.
>> Group hug?
We can do that for you.
>> I'll take a group hug.
>> That you can get.
>> Get in here.
>> Get a Shambo.
>> I'm down with that.
I love these guys, but I wanted
that rib eye.
I wanted that steak.
I need that steak.
I need that protein.
>> I'm so disappointed in
myself.
>> You know, I was surprised.
I thought Ashley would be just
fine in today's challenge, but
she's the one that lost it for
us.
Like, come on.
It's just one of those things.
You got to suck it up.
>> I've never been so close to
passing out in my entire life.
>> It's nothing that's going to
hurt you.
It just tastes bad.
I feel like sometimes she's not
carrying her weight.
>> I don't think I would have
finished.
>> I'm an easy target, though.
>> Well, don't worry about it,
because I'm...
You are a rock star.
You had, like, this much left.
I almost threw up.
>> I'm so happy you're out here
with me.
>> I'm so happy you're out here,
too.
>> You have no idea.
I'm very disappointed in myself.
I tried, but my body, like,
literally couldn't take it.
I threw up immediately.
Like, I could not get it down.
I put all the blame on myself.
It sucks.
I tried. I mean...
>> You did so...
You know what?
You did so good.
I'm really proud of you.
You stepped it up, for sure.
>> I mean, honestly, you're
helping me get through it.
>> Oh.
After the challenge, Ashley felt
horrible, but...
You know, she felt like it was
her fault, but you know what?
We're kind of... kind of like
sisters, so we've kind of been
able to talk each other through
that and encourage each other,
so, you know, I just wanted to
make her feel better about it.
I hope I can pick you up and...
>> Yeah...
>> You know that you're strong.
And you've done well.
You've done really, really well.
I'm really proud of you.
(birds screeching)
>> Get that fire going.
Get some water.
>> Quick order of business,
crew.
If people were to ask me, well,
it really sucked that I sent
Shambo over to the tribe so she
couldn't partake in the feast...
Well, it really sucked when she
lost our chicken.
>> I agree.
>> All right?
>> Yeah, right.
>> So, this should clean her
slate, but she had to suffer
some consequences for losing a
food source.
So, let's eat!
(whooping)
>> So we come back from the
reward challenge.
We got all this food.
Everybody's ready, and it's,
like, let's eat.
>> Catch!
>> But Chief jumps in and starts
messing up the fire, getting...
doing a bum job of it.
>> Any dry husks anywhere?
>> No, all of this husk is wet.
I just want to eat the thing.
I'm damn near getting tempted to
eat it raw...
>> Ah.
>> ...'cause this is bogus.
>> You need three things for
fire.
You need the spark, you need
air, and you need fuel...
>> Dave, you do a lot of
talking, but not a lot of
action.
>> Is that right?
>> Yeah, you do, man.
Just do it.
>> It's funny, 'cause I was the
one who started the fire first.
>> Well, come on. Help us, dude.
>> Okay. No, no... (muttering)
I don't want to do that, because
you'll just be, like, "All
right, let me keep playing with
it."
>> I'm not in the mood for
suggestions.
I'm in the mood for help.
After we get this started...
>> All you got to do is ask,
man.
All you got to do is ask.
>> If anyone thinks they can
start the fire, jump in, don't
hold back.
>> No.
>> No, I didn't ask...
Was I asked for help?
>> Well, if you can start it,
start it, you know.
>> I got to hear it from
the chief.
>> No, you don't.
You're a grown ass man.
>> Man, I'm not even trying to
be arrogant.
It's just that I sometimes
patronize people without
thinking about it, but I'm
afraid that I'm going to shoot
myself in the foot without
knowing what's happening.
Hey, Chief, I'm sorry about
being a jerk, dude.
>> Don't worry about it.
>> All right. Shake?
>> It's all good, man.
>> All right.
>> I'd love to.
>> All right, good.
>> Oh.
>> Build that thing up, Dave.
Come on.
>> Ow! Whooey, that's hot.
Get down.
>> Good job, guys!
>> Dave's the man!
>> Dave did it.
>> Dave, that's awesome!
>> Apparently, nobody here knows
how to make fire but me, which
to me is, like, really?
>> All right, so what are we
doing?
What are we doing?
>> But I'm trying to downplay
my awesomeness, 'cause it speaks
for itself.
Actions speak louder than words,
so I don't need to say anything.
>> Oh, my gosh, that looks so
good.
>> Oh, my God.
(laughter)
(whooping)
>> You know, hey, if I'm the
only guy here that can make
fire, makes me pretty valuable.
>> They are in trouble.
I could take the whole...
After I finish this, I could
take the whole team by myself.
(birds singing)
>> Hey, you guys, I'm going to
share the clues with you to the
hidden immunity idol.
>> Nice.
>> 'Cause you're more of a damn
tribe to me than my tribe is.
(laughter)
The third clue is, "Turn your
gaze downward, scour the earth
and take heed.
Inside the hole of the tree is
the idol you need."
Which is this tree right here.
>> By the fire.
Shambo-- she's still looking for
the immunity idol.
>> But she will never find it.
(Russell laughs)
It's in my pocket.
So that's funny.
>> Jaison, do you have the
hidden immunity idol?
>> No, I don't have it.
Would I tell you if I had it?
>> I hope so.
>> I know damn well Ben got
kicked out with that freaking
idol, idiot.
>> Oh, I agree.
>> I know he did.
>> But he didn't play it, so...
>> I know.
>> The immunity idol was never
played, even if Ben had it.
I mean, I know somebody has it,
and I have a feeling, if it
wasn't Ben, it's Russell, and I
have a feeling it's probably
Russell.
>> Yeah, I've been in that tree
a lot, but not all the way up in
it. Where is it?
>> You don't have to go all the
way up in it.
She didn't stand up in it.
I'm telling you.
You are lying to me.
>> Why is this so much of a
concern for you?
>> Because I want...
>> Why are you so worried about
this?
>> Because I feel like you
should be honest.
>> You're freaking me out right
now, 'cause I'm telling you the
truth, and you're telling me I'm
not honest.
>> Well...
>> You want to be the one who
goes next?
You're throwing all kind of
stupid stuff around.
Liz, she gets it.
She knows what's going on.
But why in the world would you
threaten me?
That's like slapping me in the
face.
You don't think I'm going to
get back at you?
Girl, you're walking on that
thin ice.
>> Ben... Ben told me...
>> I'm going to tell you that
right now.
Let me tell you.
You're walking on thin ice,
period.
>> Oh, God.
There's been a lot of rain
tonight, like torrential
downpour, and it's freezing.
Now all our blankets are wet.
I'm actually regretting the
decision to choose blankets
instead of the tarp right now.
This is the hardest night yet.
It's bad.
(bird singing)
>> Come on, boys.
Right there.
(grunts)
Tree mail, baby.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Oh.
Tree mail.
>> "Some hold on for their lives
while others will attack.
So who gets the glory, and who
gets the sack?
Obviously, in this challenge,
you'll have to kick some butts.
Not worried about going home
tonight?
Then you must be plain nuts."
>> For the past 24 hours, I
haven't really thought about
the game.
I've just been trying to focus
on, uh, staying dry, but, you
know, today is a huge challenge.
It's the first immunity
challenge after we lost the
last immunity challenge, so we
really want to reclaim this and
keep up our advantage.
So I'm hoping people will
forget about their discomfort
and just hit it hard today.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, Shambo, you can
return to your tribe, Galu.
That doesn't look like a very
nice welcome from Galu, Shambo.
Other than Erik, nobody even
acknowledged you coming back.
>> It's a game.
I wouldn't take it personally.
It's raining, and everyone's
trying to stay warm.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Foa Foa, I'll take back
immunity.
>> Let's go, guys.
We can get this.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, one man
and one woman from both tribes
will each hold on to a rope
connected to a net while
members of the other tribe
attempt to shoot coconuts into
that net.
The more coconuts go into the
net, the heavier the net becomes
until you can no longer hold on.
The tribe member who holds on to
their net the longest wins
immunity for their tribe.
Losers go to Tribal Council
where somebody will be voted
out of this game.
Galu, you have three extra
members.
You're sitting three people out.
You cannot sit out the same
people in back-to-back
challenges.
You need to sit out two men and
one woman.
>> All right, I'm going to sit
out Dave.
>> You want out, Sham?
>> Mm.
>> Sham wants out.
>> Sham.
>> I have to.
>> And Brett.
>> PROBST: All right, Dave,
Brett, Shambo, sitting this one
out.
Take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right.
Holding the ropes for Foa Foa,
it is Liz and Russell.
For Galu, it's Russell and
Laura.
Here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Let's go, Galu!
>> PROBST: The faster you get
coconuts in the basket, the
heavier they get.
>> Come on down, Galu!
You guys got it!
>> PROBST: Kelly, right off the
bat, scores for Galu.
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: John scores for Galu.
>> Good job, John!
>> PROBST: Jaison is short.
Mick way short.
John with another toss on
Russell.
(indistinct shouting)
>> PROBST: And it connects.
>> John Boy!
>> Good job, Johnny!
>> PROBST: Natalie's short.
Jaison's short.
Foa Foa has yet to get one
coconut in.
John going for two, and John
connects again for Galu.
>> Yeah!
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: Jaison with the first
hit for Foa Foa.
Mick way short again.
Galu is on fire.
They can't miss.
>> Whoa!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa needs to pick
it up.
>> Oh, geez.
>> PROBST: Rain really coming
down now.
(loud, rumbling thunder)
>> PROBST: Erik tosses a three,
and it lands on Liz's.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: She does not like it.
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Kelly scores for
Galu.
Erik scores for Galu.
John scores for Galu.
Russell holding a lot of weight
in that net for Foa Foa.
Foa Foa, you need to double-time
it.
Ashley hasn't made a single
shot yet.
Jaison piling on Russell now.
>> Doing good, Russ!
Hold on, baby!
>> PROBST: Natalie connects.
>> Knock 'em dead, John.
>> PROBST: John with another
toss and another hit.
Russell struggling to hang on.
(grunting)
>> PROBST: This might do it from
Erik.
Nope. Russell's still fighting.
(Russell breathes loudly)
>> PROBST: John trying to put
Russell out of it.
He connects.
Russell digging deep.
(Russell grunts)
Another one from Erik.
That might do it, and it does.
Russell's out of the challenge.
(overlapping shouting)
>> PROBST: Liz, the last
remaining hope for Foa Foa.
>> Come on, Liz!
>> PROBST: Liz going to have to
dig deep and outlast Russell
and Laura.
>> Let's go, Galu.
We've got it, guys.
>> PROBST: Mick puts one in on
Russell.
Erik just misses.
>> Oh!
>> Good job, Liz!
>> PROBST: Liz doing a great job
keeping Foa Foa in this.
Jaison connects!
Russell now struggling for Galu.
>> It's a wrap.
>> PROBST: Erik calling it.
>> PROBST: Is this enough?
>> Come on, Liz!
>> PROBST: Liz giving everything
she has.
Is this enough from John?
Liz struggling to hang on.
>> Russell, hang out, Russell.
Hang out.
>> Good job, Liz.
Good job, Liz!
>> PROBST: John puts another one
in.
>> Good job, G.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Liz out of the
challenge!
Galu wins immunity!
>> Yeah!
>> Hell, yeah!
Good job, boy.
>> Thank you.
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: Galu,
congratulations.
Once again, immunity is yours.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: No Tribal Council
tonight.
Nobody else going home from
Galu.
Russell, Liz, Jaison, Ashley,
Mick, Natalie, after 14 days,
one of you will be voted out at
tonight's Tribal Council.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
(rolling thunder)
>> Today is the first day I'm
convinced that we might be at
a real serious disadvantage.
You know, it just doesn't...
As a tribe, it doesn't look
good anymore.
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> It's okay.
>> I'm sorry, sweetie.
>> Our shelter's got rain in it.
None of us slept last night.
We're all cold.
We're all tired.
Our hands and feet look like
crap.
This is absolute misery.
I have never in my life been
this cold, had my hands this
destroyed, and my feet look so
miserable in my life.
There's nothing I want to do
more right now than to get out
of here.
(loud, rumbling thunderclaps)
>> No.
>> I know I don't want to go.
>> Normally, before Tribal
Council, we all get to run
around and scramble, trying to
figure out strategy, but
today...
I mean, we're all cooped up in a
shelter right now.
We... I can't do much about it
without other people hearing.
It's either we all just vote
for whoever we think, and
everyone just pack your bags, or
we talk about it and figure it
out so the person knows who's
going home.
>> It will be an interesting
Tribal.
I have no idea what everyone
else is going to do.
I'm going to vote for Liz.
I haven't really had a trust
with her since day one.
I always thought there was
something weird going on with
her, so I just don't trust her.
>> I think Ashley should go.
She, to me, is the physical
weakest link.
I just don't think she pulled
her weight in the challenges.
>> We got to send somebody home
tonight.
Because the guys are pretty
tight-- possibly Liz, possibly,
uh, Ashley, um, or Natalie.
I'll play it by ear.
>> We're all stuck in the
shelter, confined in a little
ball, so I don't know what
everybody's decision is going
to be, but I think it's going
to be one of us girls, for sure.
>> I have absolutely no idea
what's going to go down with
this vote.
My mentality right now is just
to go into Tribal Council and
see what happens.
>> It bums me out that I had to
stop my strategy because of the
rain.
That's not playing the game like
I would regularly play it.
(thunder crashing)
Liz asked me if I had the
immunity idol, and she just
keeps telling me that she don't
trust me.
You know, when you come at me
like that, and you tell me you
don't trust me, it puts a target
on your back.
But Liz is stronger than Ashley.
So I-I don't really know which
way I'm going to go tonight.
>> PROBST: Jaison, finish this
sentence for me.
"Until Survivor, the toughest
thing I'd ever gone through
was..."
>> If I had to make a
comparison, there was, uh, you
know, when I was playing on the
U.S.A. National team...
>> PROBST: In what sport?
>> Uh, in water polo.
We had this Yugoslavian coach
who believed that our body
needed to be in crisis at all
times, so we're jumping in the
pool and wrestling with another
guy, then jumping out and doing
circuits of just beating up on
each other, for eight, nine
hours a day, seven days a week.
So, I came in here thinking that
this wasn't going to be that big
a deal because I had done a lot
of training and done a lot of
things I thought were hard, but
this is by far the hardest
thing I've ever done.
>> PROBST: Ashley, I'm guessing
coming to Tribal was almost
welcome, simply because there is
a warm fire here and cover from
the rain.
>> Yeah, that's true, because
we're all so cold.
Our clothes are drenched.
I mean, it sucks sending
someone home, but at the same
time, hey, at least there's
going to be a fire tonight.
>> And the fact that we're also,
like, stuck under this little
shelter and it's pouring rain.
I mean, it's pretty tough to
scramble, you know, when we're
all sitting there watching each
other.
You can only be so subtle.
What, are you gonna pull
somebody out in the rain?
They'd be like, "Hell, no, I'm
not going with you.
It's freezing out there.
Are you mad?
You're going home, man, that's
it."
>> PROBST: Natalie, that's got
to be a little uncomfortable,
knowing that maybe they decided,
"You know what?
The girl in the yellow dress-- I
guess I'm gonna vote for her."
>> That's true.
There was no way to try and
strategize.
Literally we're, like, purple.
Before, it was always a
scramble, so I think the weather
had a lot to do with it today.
>> PROBST: Russell, does the
criteria for voting begin to
change when you look at what
you've been through and what you
might have to go through?
Does suddenly competition at
challenges give way to: who do I
really like being around or who
can I trust?
>> Yeah, I think it does.
We are down to five people now,
and I think to me, it depends on
who you can trust.
That's like gold in this game.
But the fact of the matter is: I
really trust the people around
me right now.
>> PROBST: So that's the
problem.
>> And that's the problem.
Right.
>> PROBST: Ashley, Russell talks
about trusting everybody at this
point.
Who do you trust in this tribe?
>> I trust everyone to a certain
extent, but I think my biggest
trust lies in Natalie and
Russell.
>> PROBST: What is it about
Russell you trust?
>> From the get-go, he's kind of
pulled me under his wing a
little bit.
I don't know, I just feel like I
can talk to him.
So, from the get-go, that's why
we have had-- kind of had a
different connection.
>> PROBST: Liz, who do you
trust?
>> I trust pretty much everyone
here.
I think in going through three
Tribal Councils and enduring all
the losses that we've had to
endure, it's brought us much
more closer together than I ever
would have anticipated and I am
surprised that I would place so
much trust in these guys, but I
do.
>> PROBST: So you'd be shocked
if it was you tonight?
>> I would be surprised, but
it's my gut that would tell me,
and, you know, that's not an
issue about trust.
>> PROBST: Mick, how will this
tribe be better when they go
back to camp tonight?
>> In the long haul, maybe we'll
be a little more organized.
Maybe we'll be a little bit
stronger at challenges.
You know, eventually I think
that will strengthen us.
>> PROBST: Jaison, you agree
with that?
>> I think so.
I mean, depending on who leaves,
we could be a stronger team
physically.
We could end up being a weaker
team because somebody is hurt
that their person went and they
didn't think they were supposed
to.
>> PROBST: Russell, do you like
the feeling as we get ready to
vote?
It's so up in the air.
It's a wild card.
Who knows what everybody else is
going to do?
>> Yeah, it doesn't make sense
and that's not how you play the
game, but with this group, I
think we're just too tight, so I
don't really think it's up in
the air.
>> PROBST: We'll find out if
you're right.
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to vote.
Mick, you're up.
>> I trust you the least out of
everyone.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Ashley.
Liz.
Ashley.
Two votes-- Ashley, one vote--
Liz.
Ashley.
That's three votes-- Ashley, one
vote-- Liz.
Fifth person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa-- Ashley.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Ashley, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Kick some butt, you guys.
>> PROBST: Well, you're now down
to five members.
The question is: can you dig
deep enough to do what needs to
be done to turn this game
around?
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
The storms continue to batter
both tribes.
>> The elements out here-- like,
it's going to break you down.
(Jaison laughs, thunder cracks)
>> PROBST: And another castaway
goes down.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Everybody, hold up.
Medical!
Hold where you are.
>> Survivor was the hardest
thing I've ever done in my
entire life, but it was the best
experience.
I have learned so much about
myself.
I am such a high-maintenance
girl at home.
I never thought in a million
years that I would be able to
go through the things that I've
gone through here.
I wish that my tribe would beat
Galu and take some wins, and
hopefully one of them can win
the million dollars.