>> JEFF PROBST: Deep in the
heart of the South Pacific lies
one of the most mysterious and
isolated islands in the world,
Samoa.
A land that's steep, volcanic
mountains, towering waterfalls,
fierce rainstorms.
Rugged coastlines, virtually
untouched by civilization.
And surrounded by an ocean
that's home to a diverse marine
life.
Here's where these 20 Americans
are beginning the adventure
of a lifetime.
Though they've not yet spoken,
first impressions are already
forming.
>> This lady with her free-
flowing mullet, she's probably
some super outdoors woman that
will naturally step forward as
our leader.
>> Dude, I'm a people magnet.
People have gravitated to me my
entire life.
It's like, "Ooh, my God!
This chick rocks!
We love her."
>> There's a guy who looks as
tough as nails.
He looks like a pit bull.
He's like...
I wouldn't want to mess with
him, that's for sure.
>> I plan on making it as
miserable as possible, making
it hell for everybody to get
what I want.
>> When I first started being a
police officer, I believed
every single person I met.
But now, I don't believe
anybody anymore.
>> PROBST: 20 strangers forced
to work together while battling
the elements and each other.
They must learn to adapt or
they'll be voted out.
In the end, only one will
remain to claim the
million-dollar prize.
39 days, 20 people, one
survivor.
>> PROBST: Welcome to Survivor:
Samoa.
You guys have already been
divided into two tribes--
wearing purple, you are Galu;
wearing yellow, you are Foa Foa.
You are now going to make your
first tribe decision.
You are going to elect a leader
for your tribe.
Out here in Samoa, the leaders,
or matais as they're called,
are held in very high esteem
because they're called upon to
protect the interests of their
tribe.
Whoever you elect is going to
do that for your tribe.
It's going to be based on body
language, observations.
A piece of parchment and a pen
for each of you.
Do your best to describe who
looks like they could lead your
tribe.
>> It's like, "Ah!
Kind of like a deer in
headlights."
Taking on a leadership role in
a game like Survivor is a
death wish.
>> PROBST: Once you have it,
you can head back to your mat.
>> I do have leadership
qualities.
Being in the operating room,
you have to make snap decisions.
It takes more than a note from
Mom to get through med school
and residency.
>> PROBST: All right, Galu, who
looks like they could lead your
tribe?
>> I voted for the guy in the
gray shirt with the very short
cut.
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Erik.
>> PROBST: First vote is for
Erik.
Guy in the back.
>> I voted for the lady with
the purple bandanna.
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Shambo.
>> PROBST: Shambo?
>> Yup.
My nickname has been Shambo
since '86.
I was in the United States
Marine Corps, and Rambo had the
same bandanna I had.
So everybody was like,
Shannon, Shambo, Rambo, Shambo,
so that's my game name, and
that's what I'm here to do,
is play.
>> PROBST: All right, woman in
front with the blond hair.
>> Black jacket and dreads
right here.
>> What's your name?
>> Russell.
>> That's one vote for Russell.
In the back.
>> I voted for the guy with the
dreadlocks-- Russell.
>> PROBST: Two votes for Russell
>> Handsome man in the suit.
>> PROBST: All right, that's
three votes Russell.
Russell, who did you vote for?
>> Shambo.
>> PROBST: Shambo.
So Russell has three votes,
Shambo has two.
Woman here in front in gray.
>> Shambo.
>> Guy in the back?
>> Russell.
>> PROBST: That's four for
Russell, Three for Shambo.
Erik.
>> Yeah, better looking Lennox
Lewis.
>> PROBST: That's five for
Russell, that will do it.
Shambo has the last vote.
>> This fellow.
>> PROBST: All right.
Russell is the leader of Galu.
All right.
Foa Foa, your turn.
>> Red shirt, jeans, khaki
jacket.
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Mick.
>> PROBST: Tall guy in the back.
>> PROBST: Mick.
That's two for Mick.
Right up here in the front with
the cap.
>> Girl in the orange shirt
with white flowers.
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Marisa.
>> PROBST: Brought a smile to
your face.
That's two for Mick, one for
Marisa.
Mick.
>> The yellow shirt and vest.
>> PROBST: What's your name?
>> Jaison.
>> PROBST: All right.
Right here in the front, in the
yellow dress.
>> The guy in the khaki jacket
and orange shirt.
>> PROBST: That's three
for Mick.
Jaison, who'd you vote for?
>> The girl with the dark hair,
Asian.
>> The name is Liz.
>> PROBST: All right, Marisa,
who did you vote for?
>> Short, strong guy with the
hat.
>> PROBST: Short, strong guy--
what's your name?
>> Russell.
>> PROBST: Woman in front.
>> Male, gray vest, yellow
button up-- Jaison.
>> PROBST: Down here on the end.
>> The tall, nicely dressed,
Yale-type black man.
>> PROBST: All right, we have a
tie, now.
We have Mick with three votes,
Jaison with three votes.
One vote left.
Last vote, hold it up.
>> Guy with green jacket, red
shirt, Mick.
>> PROBST: That's it.
We have a leader for Foa Foa.
It is Mick.
>> I really wasn't surprised I
wasn't written down as the
leader, but I don't really see
anybody else that's a country
boy.
I've shot and killed and
cleaned about everything you're
allowed to in Missouri, and
probably a few things
you're not.
So I've done all this stuff
before, and I think a lot of
these people are kind of candy
asses.
>> PROBST: All right, leaders,
now, you're going to make your
first big decision.
And it will test your
leadership skills right from
the start.
>> I'm scared.
This leadership thing can go
south real quick.
The highest nail definitely
gets pounded down in this game.
And right now, I'm, like, sky
high.
>> PROBST: All right, you're now
going to make your first big
decisions as leaders.
You're going to decide who's
going to participate in our
opening challenge.
Mick, I want you to choose from
your tribe who you think is
your best swimmer.
>> Okay.
Jaison.
He looks like a swimmer.
>> Everybody assumes that tall,
black guy can't swim, so I
didn't think in a hundred years
that Mick would choose me for
the swimming.
But I played water polo through
college and the national team,
so I would like to claim I'm a
pretty good swimmer.
>> PROBST: Russell, who do you
think is your best swimmer?
>> I'm choosing the young,
Brazilian-looking guy.
>> PROBST: John, head on over.
Mick, pick the strongest
person on your tribe.
>> I'm choosing Russell.
>> PROBST: Russell.
All right, for Galu.
>> I'm going to choose the
younger guy with the short-
cropped haircut.
>> PROBST: Erik?
>> Erik.
>> PROBST: Mick, pick who you
think is your most agile person.
>> I'm choosing Marissa?
>> Marisa.
>> PROBST: All right, Russell.
>> I'm choosing my African
queen with braids.
>> PROBST: All right, Yasmin,
come on over.
Yasmin wearing nice heels.
All right, Mick, last choice.
Pick the smartest person on
this tribe.
>> This is tough.
I am choosing the woman on
the end.
I'm sorry, I lost your name.
>> Liz.
>> I forgot.
>> PROBST: Liz.
>> I think Mick chose me
because I'm Asian, and while I
certainly don't take offense to
the positive attributes of
being an Asian, because they're
smart, they're supposed to be
studious.
>> PROBST: Come on over.
Join your tribe.
>> There are also negative
attributes like sneaky,
conniving, and I just don't
want people attributing all the
negative attributes to me.
>> PROBST: All right, Russell,
who do you think is the
smartest?
>> I'm choosing Shambo!
>> Oh, my God!
I am smart in the ways of life,
but as far as book smart, dear,
God, please, help me here.
>> PROBST: Come on over.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to the first challenge?
Here's how it's going to work.
On my "go," the designated
swimmer will swim out, retrieve
a key, and swim back.
The designated strong person
will use that key to unlock a
chain, freeing up two very
heavy bundles of logs.
You'll then carry those logs
back to the mat where the most
agile person will use those
logs to get up to a balance
beam.
You must maneuver across the
balance beam while navigating
another key through a rope maze.
The designated smart person
will use that key to unlock a
bag of puzzle pieces, using the
pieces to solve the puzzle.
First tribe to solve the puzzle
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Fire, in the form of
flint.
>> Let's get it, guys.
>> PROBST: Huge advantage to
start this game.
Take your spots, we'll get
started.
All right, here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
The first leg is a swimming
leg.
Wow, two sprinters through the
water.
Got to swim all the way out,
retrieve the key, and get back.
Jaison starting to pull away
from John.
Mick feeling very good about
his choice for a swimmer.
>> Jaison, he surprised the
(bleep) out of me.
Afro-Americans aren't known to
be... swimmers, you know.
>> Jaison!
>> All right, come on, baby!
>> Come on, get it done!
Get it done!
>> PROBST: John now at his key.
(cheers)
Jaison has his key
and he's heading back.
John has his key.
He's heading back.
We've got a race.
>> Push it!
Push it!
>> Come on, John!
Keep going!
>> Jaison first back for Foa
Foa, passes off the key to
Russell.
Now the strong guy going to
work.
Got to unlock that chain.
That is a long swim.
>> John shanked that swim so
bad I was ready to vote him off
right there.
>> Come on, keep going!
>> PROBST: Erik has the key.
Erik now getting to work.
(cheering)
Russell having no problem with
that first bundle of logs.
(cheering)
Erik trying to make up some
time.
>> Come on, Erik!
>> PROBST: Erik now has that
first bundle.
(Erik yells)
Adrenaline coursing through that
body!
>> Push it, baby!
You got it!
All right, get back that other
one.
Look at him-- he's strong but
he's tired!
He's out of shape!
>> PROBST: Russell having a
little trouble with that second
one.
These are heavy bundles of logs.
(cheering)
Erik carrying it.
>> Come on, Erik!
>> Come on, Erik, come on!
>> PROBST: Erik down.
Russell has it.
(Russell groans)
Marisa's on the balance beam
now.
Got to make your way across the
beam while maneuvering that key
through the rope maze.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: Erik still working
with that second log.
Step by step.
>> Dig it in, baby, dig it in!
>> PROBST: Erik not giving up!
(Erik screaming)
>> Finish it, finish it!
Finish it!
>> PROBST: Erik has it!
>> Look at how Erik carried that
weight.
He made me so proud.
He had the heart of a tiger.
>> PROBST: Yasmin making up a
lot of ground for Galu.
>> That's what I'm talking
about.
>> You got it, girl, you got it.
>> PROBST: Marisa very close for
Foa Foa.
>> Good job!
Get to that bit!
>> PROBST: Marisa finishes.
Liz now unlocks the lock.
>> Don't quit.
Take your time.
>> PROBST: Liz working on the
puzzle for Foa Foa.
>> Come on.
>> Bring it to me, baby, bring
it to me.
>> There you go.
>> PROBST: There it is.
Yasmin has it.
Shambo now unlocking the puzzle
pieces.
>> Come on, Shambo.
You can still take it, baby.
You're in it.
It ain't over.
>> PROBST: Liz has had a nice
head start.
Shambo is right in it.
She was worried if she was going
to be smart enough.
>> Come on, come on!
>> PROBST: Shambo making up a
lot of time.
Shambo making up a ton of time
for Galu.
Liz very close.
Foa Foa wins reward!
(cheering)
>> We won the challenge because
Mick made a very good choice on
all legs.
>> That was amazing.
You owned it.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa, your reward.
Fire and a map to your new home.
Russell, at all frustrated?
>> No, Jeff.
I'm proud of this team.
I am not frustrated in the
least.
>> Everybody loves an underdog,
Jeff.
>> That's right.
>> PROBST: You are definitely
the underdogs.
Here's your map to your new
home.
Grab your stuff.
Head out.
You've got a camp to build.
>> Pretty boy.
Maybe he couldn't swim, but get
your ass off the mat.
Stand up.
Unbelievable.
He doesn't deserve to be here.
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
>> Oh!
>> I'm Betsy.
>> Mike.
>> How you doing?
>> Leader.
>> What do we do now?
>> Well, does anybody have any,
like, practical, real world
experience?
>> I'm a hillbilly, man.
>> Really?
>> I've done this lots of times.
The bathroom should definitely
not be up from camp.
It should be away.
>> Ben's an interesting cat.
You know, he shows up to camp
and, I mean, the guy is just,
like, "All eyes to me."
>> We just need four holes that
are, like, equidistant apart,
like...
>> I can dig, I can dig holes.
>> ...ten by ten, 12 by 12,
whatever it is.
>> I think the leadership thing
is difficult and I'm still
trying to sort out exactly how
to run it.
>> Put that other piece of
bamboo that way.
>> If he wants to step up and
take control of things, you know
what?
Have at it, my friend, because
he'll paint his own target.
>> I didn't come here to work, I
came here to play.
You got to talk about alliance
as soon as you step on this
island, so my strategy is to be
able to have a secret alliance
with each one of these dumb
girls.
We can have something like a
secret alliance.
>> Okay.
>> Hmm?
>> So we can be strong from the
beginning.
We can look back at this moment
right now...
(Ashley laughs)
...and say, "We did it from the
beginning, from day one."
>> Right.
>> It is day one now.
I've got an alliance with the
dumb, short-haired blonde.
>> This is what I wanted.
>> Pinky swear?
>> I wanted someone to approach
me.
>> And the even dumber long-
haired blonde.
>> I'll trust you.
So do I have that same trust
with you?
>> Yes.
>> And the dark-haired girl...
>> You've got my word.
>> You have mine.
>> I like to call it my dumb-
ass girl alliance.
It's just gonna be me and you.
>> All right.
>> I told them exactly the same
thing.
This is real.
>> I believe you.
>> Not joking.
And I believe they're just
gullible enough to believe it.
I know this ... before I even
got here.
Align with the old lady.
(Betsy laughs)
>> You suck.
>> To make sure that I win this
game, my fourth alliance is with
the old lady.
I know she's a lot smarter than
my dumb-ass girl alliance, so
I've got to be real careful with
that one.
>> Should we shake?
Should we let people see us
shake or what?
That is fun, Russell.
As a police officer, I usually
can get a pretty good read on
somebody by talking to them,
looking in their eyes, their
body language.
I just have a feeling that I
don't trust Russell because he
came to me too quick in the
game.
I did make an alliance with him,
but I don't trust him.
>> Galu!
Welcome home, guys!
(cheering and applause)
>> Home, sweet home.
>> Oh, my God.
So, listen to this.
Let's make our structure.
I've been elected leader of the
Galu tribe.
It is a heavy, heavy liability.
Who's the one that you always
want to get when you don't know
who you want to get?
Get the leader.
This is almost like we're
building a raft.
Let's think about a raft, right,
on the ground, right, and then
we're going to raise the raft
up.
>> That sounds great.
>> So, make sense?
Let's get it done.
>> When we first landed on the
beach, I saw Russell, our tribe
leader, begin to actually take
charge.
It was really cool.
I felt, "Yay, we do have a
leader."
>> I just want to do some
building.
>> Ow.
>> You're going to make this
load bearing?
The tree isn't vertical, so it
isn't compressed through the
core.
>> Oh, my God.
They're still discussing it.
My only problem right now is we
have some really strong, male,
dominant personalities that
aren't hearing one another.
>> I mean, can we go higher than
this potentially?
I mean...
>> Yeah, there is no limitation.
>> This isn't necessarily like a
hard stop line...
>> No, no.
>> There's no reason we
couldn't...
>> Yeah, exactly.
I'm just sweeping this...
>> ...go up here and then two
stacks, like five and then five.
>> They got all hung up on
exactly what should be done,
how, when, where.
>> If we're going to sleep here,
right, and then build a
trench... and all the drain--
all the water that runs off this
hill, which was part of the
initial rationale for picking
this spot, right, gets diverted
around us.
In my life experience, a little
bit of planning has taught me
don't always be so quick to
start spinning the wheels.
Raw destruction.
Everyone's in a hurry right now.
>> I know.
>> We've got all day.
This isn't your typical
construction job.
You can't push your schedule to
the right, come in late, and
deliver over budget, because
guess what.
Your budget is coconuts.
>> Should we start...?
>> I think we-- it might be
suited to take, like, a five-
minute break and just really
think about what we're doing
here.
>> Oh, my God, these guys are
killing me.
John is very much all talk, no
business.
I think he's an engineer or
something.
He's, he's too technical.
>> I think wind needs to be
addressed.
I think rain is your biggest
adversary.
>> All he's doing is running
his mouth.
>> I'm trying to kind of get an,
get an inventory of all the
actions that we need to have
completed or at least try.
>> I think we ought to just act
and quit freaking thinking.
>> Okay.
>> Ooh, Lord have mercy.
>> I'm tired.
>> I'm going to go get wet.
>> Yeah, yeah, let's go.
>> Yeah, because I'm vile.
(laughter)
>> Oh, these young kids.
I didn't want to go in the damn
water.
It's crazy, because I have to
constantly remind myself, this
is not the Marine Corps, and all
these people are in their mid-
20s, so the way that the rest of
the tribe does things is going
to be way different than the way
that I do things.
So Russell as leader-- I-I'm
struggling with it.
He's not being assertive.
He's not leading right now, in
my opinion.
He needs to open a can of whoop-
ass and lay some laws down.
That's what I would have done.
That would have been my game
plan.
>> I lived in New Orleans, in
St. Bernard Parish, right by the
levee.
The storm was a category 5.
When it hit, it broke the levee.
I was in my house.
Me-- I have a German shepherd.
His name was Rocky.
And I tried to get out of the
house, and I realized I wasn't
going to make it.
So I grabbed my ax, because as a
fireman, one thing you learn is
when you go in something, you
have to be able to get out.
By the time I got upstairs, the
water was rushing in, like...
>> Oh, my God.
>> I look at Rocky.
You know, I couldn't even see
him.
It was muddy water.
He was gone.
I can't even find him.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh, my God, oh.
>> So sad.
>> I never lived in New Orleans
and I'm not a fireman.
I never even had a German
shepherd.
You know, I really ain't got
that close to another dog yet.
I had him for, like, nine years.
>> Really?
I'm such an animal lover.
That was so hard for me to hear,
and, I don't know, it just kind
of gets to you.
>> And when I got on the roof, I
stayed there for two days.
>> Really?
>> Two days.
And it's crazy how you can break
their hearts by telling them a
lie.
>> Russell is an interesting
character because I really
trusted him off the start, but
he's really been scrambling with
everyone, and he was trying to
get people's sympathy about
Katrina, which is probably very
true, and his dog, and I don't
want to diminish that story, but
I just think that it was-- he
was angling at stuff, and I'm
starting to feel like he's
pretty slimy.
>> I figure I'll make it a
little interesting for
everybody when they wake up.
I emptied all the water out of
all the canteens.
I plan on weeding out the weak
right off the bat.
I plan on making it as
miserable as possible for
everybody.
Little stuff like taking a sock,
I done burn it in the fire.
I think if I can control how
they feel, I can control how
they think.
I'm really a multi-millionaire.
I own an oil company in Houston.
I'm not here for the money.
I'm only here to show people
how easy it is to win this game.
Another accomplishment complete.
I'm the worst one to trust out
here.
I should be the first one to go.
But I'm going to do everything
it takes to win this game.
>> There's no more water.
>> None whatsoever?
>> No.
>> Yeah, they're all empty.
>> Oh, you know, I haven't been
drinking.
>> Somebody drank my whole
canteen.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm looking for my socks,
which I can't seem to find.
Gone, disappeared.
Me feet are starting to hurt.
They're a little blistered, and
I'd really like to find some
socks and to be warm, finally.
>> I don't mean to be, like,
pressing, but we have to hurry.
Because we have to fill the
canteens, cook some crab up.
>> Will you just relax?
>> No, I don't want to relax.
>> It's way too hot to touch.
>> it's not that hot.
We can start pouring it.
With the coconut husk?
>> Here.
>> I'll do everything.
>> No, Liz, Liz, you want to
fill the canteen.
>> It's hot.
We can blow on it.
>> You can blow on it and in a
smaller portion it will cool it
faster.
Use a little common sense.
>> My strategy is working like
a dream.
>> We have not had sleep.
Just...
>> I slept fine.
>> Congratulations.
>> And they're hollering at
each other right now.
And I'm going to just sit back
and watch them, you know, watch
it happen.
>> I just need to keep some
serenity.
>> I'll leave you alone.
Right now, I think I am running
the whole show.
They don't even know it, but I
know I am.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
How you guys doing?
>> Good.
>> Great.
>> PROBST: Russell, how you
feeling about your tribe?
>> Best group of people I could
ever meet.
Everybody's pulling their
weight.
Everybody tough as nails.
>> Jeff, I've never read that
book.
"Things Losers Say."
>> That was really good.
That was good.
Can we start this, Jeff,
because I'm ready to open some
cans of whoop-ass.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's immunity challenge, six
members of each tribe will race
across a series of A-frames
while carrying three coils of
rope.
You will then use that rope to
pull a heavy crate to the
finish platform, where the four
remaining tribe members will
disassemble the crate and use
the pieces to solve a puzzle.
First tribe to finish wins
immunity.
>> Hmm...
>> PROBST: This is the immunity
idol.
When you have this at your camp,
you cannot go home.
Tonight the losing tribe goes to
Tribal Council.
Tonight somebody will be the
first person voted out of this
game.
All right, everybody, take your
spots, we'll get started.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Galu over in one fell swoop.
Galu off to a huge lead.
Foa Foa quickly behind.
>> Get a running start!
>> PROBST: Yasmin trying to get
over for Galu.
Russell now coming down to help.
>> You got to climb, you got to
climb.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa now working
together to get over.
Galu has all their members over
the second A-frame.
>> Go, go!
(indistinct yelling)
>> PROBST: Galu now working
together, building a human
pyramid.
Great strategy!
Foa Foa is over the second A-
frame.
>> Go.
>> Go, Foa Foa!
>> Russell, grab that rope!
>> You can do it!
>> PROBST: This last A-frame--
much more difficult because
there is no momentum.
Galu is up and Galu is over.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Some skin coming off
on that one.
Foa Foa still working.
Mick using his entire body to
support Jaison.
>> Come on, Galu!
>> You can do it!
>> Come on, Galu, let's go!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa is over.
>> Come on, Foa Foa!
You got this, guys.
>> PROBST: Both tribes now
stretching out that rope.
You've got to tie all three
ropes to the heavy crate.
Galu still in the lead.
Go, go, go, go, go!
>> Come on, guys!
>> Heave-ho, heave-ho!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa is back in
it.
It's a tug-of-war now.
(overlapping shouting)
>> You got it, you got it!
>> Go, go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Russell grunting it
out.
Galu working well together.
(overlapping shouting)
Very heavy crates.
>> Pull!
>> PROBST: Go!
Puzzle makers, start working for
Galu.
Let's go!
Go!
Puzzle makers, start working for
Foa Foa.
Galu getting a quick, early
start on putting this puzzle
together.
>> All right, you guys, what we
need to do is we need to find
writing on the top only.
>> "Survival," "survival."
>> Everybody grab a piece and
find your match.
>> Yes.
>> S-U...
>> U-- here we go.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa making some
progress.
Galu absolutely nowhere on this
puzzle.
It's like they just started.
This says "there..."
(overlapping chatter)
>> Okay, come on, we get it now.
We have it, we have it.
>> Here, here, here, here...
Here's a "V," here's a "V."
>> PROBST: Galu thinks they have
something going now.
>> Got it, got it, got it!
>> That's it.
(overlapping chatter)
>> Come on, guys, we have it.
>> PROBST: Now it's Foa Foa who
seems lost.
>> That's not it.
>> Drop it down, slide it down.
>> PROBST: Galu making a big
move now on their puzzle.
They think they have it.
Are they right?
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Shambo thinks they're
close.
Foa Foa falling further and
further behind.
>> "Without victory there is no
survival!"
>> PROBST: Galu wins immunity!
(cheering)
>> Galu, Galu, Galu is in the
house!
Galu, Galu, Galu is in the
(cheering)
>> PROBST: Galu,
congratulations.
Immunity, safe tonight at Tribal
Council.
Monica, I will give you this--
fire.
(cheering)
Foa Foa, I got nothing for you
except a date with me tonight
at Tribal Council where one of
you will be the first person
voted out of this game.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
See you at Tribal.
>> Everybody, listen.
That's only like the first
quarter in a seven-game series.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You know?
It's a long way to go.
>> Today at the challenge, we
lost, and that sucks.
I don't know whose fault it was.
I feel like, you know, we all
contributed.
I need to go in.
>> You got to make a decision
now for real.
>> We got to go in.
I don't know, I think we have a
lot to think about, but I don't
want to be the one to bring it
up because then I'm gonna have a
target on my back.
>> I think right now it's a
matter of strength.
>> I do, too.
>> I think, I think the weakest
should go.
You know?
>> So what do you think?
>> Well, weakest-wise, I think
it's Ashley, just based purely
on physical strength.
>> Yeah, I second Ashley.
>> I'm 62.
I'm the oldest one out here and,
you know, I do not want to be
the first one out, you know, so
I'm talking to a few people and
saying that I think right now we
should work on strength.
Ashley.
I'm going based on strength,
weakest.
There's going to be hard
challenges ahead of us, so I
think we should vote off the
weakest, and I am not the
physically weakest.
>> Okay, but... but you've been,
like, talking to everybody.
>> I know.
>> So I don't know why you've
been doing that, and it makes me
a little wary.
>> Does it?
>> It makes me wary, yeah,
because I've seen you talking
individually, like, to everyone.
>> So you think...
>> I'm just not sure...
>> If I'm talking individually,
it doesn't mean I'm trying to be
strategizing with them.
>> I'd rather keep it pretty
low-key.
I mean, what have you been
talking about?
>> Everything.
We're out here on Survivor.
Talking about having a good
time, talking to some of them
about what they think and who
they think the weakest...
How do you come to me and
threaten me and telling me
you're feeling uncomfortable.
Are you kidding me?
Marisa is the dumbest player
I've ever seen.
>> It is a game, you know.
>> Yeah.
I'm running the show here.
You come up to me and threaten
me, you got to go, and she's
gone.
She just completely threatened
me, saying, "You're not making
me comfortable."
I said, "Why is she telling me
this right now?"
What is that going to make me
think?
That makes me think I got to get
rid of her.
>> Okay, who?
>> Marisa.
>> No, you think so?
>> I know so.
She's going first.
>> Okay.
>> If you stay with me, then
you're going to be fine for a
long time.
Vote Marisa.
>> Really?
All right.
>> My tribe will believe
anything I tell them at any
point because they're just
stupid.
I'm starting to make her
nervous.
Why would you say that?
>> Still don't know if Marisa...
All right, good, because I can't
stand that bitch.
>> Mick's the leader of the
tribe, but I'm the one in charge
of the camp.
You can call me the puppet
master.
They can be my little puppets.
They'll run when I tell them to
run, they'll walk when I tell
them to walk.
When I'm finished with them,
just throw them in the trash.
>> I wouldn't trust Russ.
>> Why do you say that?
>> Oh, I just wouldn't.
>> Well, tell me why.
Give me a reason.
>> Oh, I don't know why.
A woman's intuition.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
approach the flame, dip it in,
and get fire.
In this game, fire represents
your life.
As long as you have fire, you
are still in the game.
When your fire's gone, so are
you.
Unfortunately, for one of you,
that will be the case tonight.
How's that feel, Ashley, hearing
that, that one of the ten of you
going home in just a few
minutes?
>> You know, it's really sad,
but that's just the way the game
works.
You know, whatever.
It is what it is.
>> PROBST: It is what it is.
Russell, why not just vote her
out now if it's not that big a
deal.
Let's get out of here.
>> I don't know how to answer
that question.
>> Well, I think tonight we all
realize that this is a dog eat
dog game, and we're all wearing
Milk Bone underwear.
So the honeymoon's over and we
have to get serious, so...
>> PROBST: Ashley, regretting
that comment at all?
>> No. It's a game.
You have to vote people out.
I think we all did our best
today.
And unfortunately, they beat us.
>> I disagree.
I thought they were lucky with
the puzzle.
>> PROBST: Lucky?
>> With the puzzle, yeah.
>> PROBST: Borassi, we'd still
be there.
You guys were nowhere close.
Liz, you were designated "the
smart person."
Was that luck today?
>> No, I don't think it was luck
on their part.
I think that we could have been
a little bit more unified.
Um, we're only as strong as our
weakest link.
>> PROBST: Betsy, who do you
think is the weak link?
>> Um...
I think Ashley's the weakest.
>> PROBST: Ashley.
>> I find it very entertaining
that she thinks I'm the weakest
link, when I am like,
cardio-wise, physically fit.
I work out tons at home.
I mean, I was climbing those
walls today.
That should have shown that
I'm fit and I don't understand
how I'm the weakest link at all.
I don't-- I don't understand
that.
>> PROBST: Marisa, who would you
say it is?
>> There's different levels of
weakness, Jeff.
So I-- I'm not...
The weakest link is not...
I mean, I'm just saying.
>> That wasn't what he asked
you.
He said who do you think it is.
Who do you think the weakest
link is?
>> I-- I don't...
>> Assert yourself and answer
the question.
It's not that hard.
>> See, they don't like each
other.
>> PROBST: That's quite clear.
>> I like Ben.
I like everybody, but Marisa.
>> PROBST: You voted for Marisa
to be the leader.
>> And she could be the leader.
She has a very strong mind.
She knows what she's talking
about, she knows how to say it.
>> PROBST: Clearly Marisa must
have told you what to do at some
point.
>> She just at one point told me
that she's starting to worry
about me, you know.
I'm walking around with
everybody in the tribe.
Well, yeah.
Doesn't mean I make an alliance
with everybody in the tribe, or
trying to stab you in the back.
But she just came right at
me, so...
>> Well, he did say to me
honesty is the most important
thing in this game.
So if I felt worried about him,
I wanted to be honest with him
and share that with him.
>> Well, as soon as she came at
me telling me that she doesn't
trust me--
>> I didn't say I didn't trust
you...
>> then immediately I can't
trust her-- immediately.
>> I said I was worried
about you.
>> Well, that's not how I
took it.
>> She's concerned for your
welfare, Russell.
>> I know.
>> Obviously in this game you're
not safe no matter what.
I would hate to go home right
now, but if I did something to
put a mark on my back, well,
then that was really dumb of me,
and I need to fix it.
And I can guarantee you it won't
happen again.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
vote.
Betsy, you're up.
>> If you play with fire, you'll
get burned.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally
the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision if final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Marisa.
Marisa.
Ashley.
That's two votes Marisa, two
votes, Ashley.
Marisa.
Ashley.
We're tied-- three votes,
Marisa, three votes Ashley.
Marisa.
Five votes Marisa, three votes
Ashley.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa-- Marisa.
That's six, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Marisa, the tribe has spoken.
Well, I know you don't need me
to tell you how bad things are
on this tribe.
Hopefully, tonight's vote solved
some of the dysfunction.
Otherwise you're going to be
seeing a lot of me at Tribal
Council.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
Next time on Survivor:
An epic battle fuels bad blood
between the tribes.
>> Listen, ignorant, why would a
dude tackle me?
>> PROBST: Stop!
Out of the challenge!
And Russell goes on the warpath.
>> She's full of crap.
She's going to pay for that
statement, I promise you.
>> Tonight's really difficult
for me to swallow.
I trusted Russell initially, but
it was a mistake to say
something to him.
Because he makes trouble, and so
he made it around me.
And I'm really sad to be going
home.
I don't hold any animosity
towards anyone and I'm grateful
to have had the experience
however short it may have been.