>> JEFF PROBST: Tonight, we'll
take a deeper look into the
adventure of a lifetime.
The castaways have endured
the mental...
...the physical, and
the emotional toll of battle.
This is the first 27 days of
Survivor: Samoa.
Survivors ready?
Go!
On the battlefield, Galu was a
powerhouse.
Galu wins immunity!
Galu wins!
While Foa Foa paid the price.
The tribe has spoken.
But a twist in the game...
>> I'm going to send my girl
Shambo.
>> Excuse me?
>> PROBST: ...sent Shambo to Foa
Foa's camp.
>> I'll take a group hug.
>> We'd like to adopt her.
I mean, she has just such great
energy.
>> PROBST: While Shambo spread
the love, Russell spread
nothing but chaos.
>> I'm telling you the truth.
You're telling me I'm not
honest?
You come up to me and threaten
me, you got to go.
>> PROBST: The tribe has
spoken.
He tore his camp apart
to find the hidden immunity
idol.
>> In the history of Survivor,
How many people found the idol
without a clue?
Boo-yah!
>> PROBST: Then Mother Nature
pushed the castaways to their
breaking point.
>> You need to sit down?
>> PROBST: And both tribes lost
a member.
>> Russ, Russ, are you with us?
Russell, Russell, wake up, mate.
>> PROBST: Galu faced the vote
just once and went into the
merge eight strong.
>> Congratulations Foa Foa and
Galu.
You are now one tribe.
>> PROBST: While the Foa Foa
four used merge to execute
Russell's plan.
>> The ones I know I can trust,
they're doing exactly like I
want them to do.
>> PROBST: And infiltrate Galu.
>> Who get grapes fed to them?
The kings do.
>> PROBST: With their backs
against the wall, Natalie
gained the trust of the Galu
women and flipped the game.
>> I don't trust Erik.
>> Erik?
>> Our Erik?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Seventh person voted
out of Survivor: Samoa and the
first member of our jury, Erik,
The tribe has spoken.
Foa Foa's stubborn
determination and Russell's
keen eye for hidden idols...
>> That easy.
>> PROBST: Enabled the four to
find the crack in the enemy
fortress.
>> Oh, my God.
It's a samurai sword.
>> PROBST: And Galu was hit
hard.
>> I ain't finished playing
just yet.
>> PROBST: Kelly, the tribe has
spoken.
Laura.
Tonight's episode will reveal
new strategies, new insights,
and new scenes all involving
your favorite castaways.
>> Oh, my God.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: 27 days ago, 20
castaways began the adventure
of a lifetime.
By navigating through the
waters of the South Pacific to
a remote coast on the islands
of Samoa.
Welcome to Survivor: Samoa.
With only their first
impressions to rely on, they
began the game by electing
chiefs for their two tribes.
The better-looking Lennox Lewis.
All right, Russell is the
leader of Galu.
Foa Foa, your turn.
>> Guy green jacket, red shirt.
>> PROBST: We have a leader for
Foa Foa.
It is Mick.
>> Galu!
Welcome home, guys!
(cheers and applause)
>> PROBST: Upon arriving at the
Galu camp, Russell's style of
leadership received a positive
following.
>> Let's get it done.
>> I felt, yay, we do have a
leader.
>> PROBST: And some early
alliances were formed.
>> I will kill for you.
You're my leader so my role is
to be your protector.
Just to make life a little bit
easier...
>> that makes it a lot easier.
>> 'Cause if they go for you,
they have to go through me.
I think Russell is a fantastic
leader and I love the fact that
I'm notched right next to him.
I don't have it make any
decisions.
I get to do all the dirty work.
I wouldn't have it any
other way.
If you're not the leader the
next best thing is to be the
triggerman.
I'm here to work for you.
That's my job.
>> Right, right.
If I have one opportunity to
protect you, then I did my job.
He's the main guy.
He's the big boss.
I'm the guy behind the guy that
you need to watch out for.
'Cause if you come to Russell,
you're going to mess with me
first.
>> PROBST: At Foa Foa, Mick was
hesitant to call the shots and
his passive guidance was sourly
noted.
>> Where were you thinking of
putting it?
Where, with the...?
>> Uh, well...
>> Was it decided?
>> Ben, what do you think, man?
>> Yeah, we should just build
it, like, simple and try to
build it as sturdy as possible.
>> As soon as Jeff said we
needed to choose a leader, the
first thing that went through
my head was just let me stay
under the radar.
And so the first thing I did
was to get rid of this and just
hang it up.
Are we biting off more than we
can chew?
What do you think?
I mean, have you done this?
>> I haven't done this.
>> my approach was kind of to
be like, what, do you think
needs to be done?"
I don't want to make it a "Ask
me what to do, I'm going to
tell you."
I think that's a little bit
dangerous right now.
>> I don't know, do you think we
should do water yet, or wait
until tomorrow?
I mean, not that we...
>> He's going to...
I don't if we need, but it
wouldn't hurt, you know?
Yeah, I think...
(sighs)
Yeah, well...
Um.
>> The captain leader, Mick,
he's doing a very bad job.
He sucks.
He can't even talk to anybody
hardly.
He's not organized.
He's not a leader.
You know, he doesn't know how
to make good decisions.
The camp's a piece of crap,
but, hey, I say good job
because I don't want to do
nothing.
I didn't come here to work.
I came here to play.
We is can have something, like,
a secret alliance.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Russell's strategic
maneuvering was always one step
ahead of his tribe.
>> My tribe will believe
anything I tell them at any
point because they're just
stupid.
You can call me the puppet
master.
They can be my little puppets.
They'll run when I tell them to
run.
They'll walk when I tell them
to walk.
When I'm finished with them,
I'll just throw them in the
trash.
>> PROBST: Under the cover of
night, Russell wreaked havoc on
his unsuspecting tribe.
>> I plan on making it as
miserable as possible for
everybody.
>> I think if I can control how
they feel, I can control how
they think.
I'm going to do everything it
takes to win this game.
>> I would prefer to have
someone next to me because it's
so cold.
Russell, you want to come sleep
next to me?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> It's funny how any girl at
any level will cuddle with you
at night because it's freezing
out here, and it is very
strategic.
If you're cuddling with them
and you're rubbing their leg or
their arm, they think, "I've
got this guy.
I got him where I want him."
You know what?
If they think they got you,
they'll keep you along for the
ride because they think, "He
really likes me.
Let's not get rid of him
because no way he's going to
vote me out."
You can have that in your back
pocket without having an
alliance with them.
By the way, I'm happily married.
>> And I have the best
boyfriend in the world.
>> You guys cuddle like you've
been married for ten years.
>> This is a game we're playing.
You're supposed to lie, cheat,
and steal.
That's how it works.
What I do out here, my ma's
going to probably be pretty
damn embarrassed.
My wife is probably going to be
pissed off.
I love my kids, my wife with
all my heart.
I wouldn't do nothing to hurt
my family.
Everything I do out here is
playing the game.
Every single thing I do is
strategic, everything.
>> PROBST: The Galu tribe
continued to better their
living quarters.
>> We can also, like, make
baskets...
He's a hairdresser!
>> PROBST: And while the younger
women easily connected with each
other, Shambo was left on the
outs.
>> Wow.
You know what we're going
to need?
What we need one of you guys to
do is we need a palm frond
split up the middle.
We need a really leafy one like
that.
>> It's definitely a social
awkwardness that she has with
everybody.
She just doesn't get when she
does something that annoys
people, she just doesn't get it.
>> We can actually go collect
coconuts and mangos and bananas
and fruit.
>> She's 45 years old and you'd
think by that time you'd get
how to interact with people,
and that frustrates me because
I don't even like to--
be around her.
>> Just throw the fronds up
there as long as they overlap.
>> I've never spent a lot of
time with somebody like Shambo.
The overt aggression, and the
overt tomboyish behavior I
think puts a lot of people off,
especially when you have pretty
girls here.
Like, the hot chicks we have
around here aren't as likely to
connect with Shambo who just is
a brute.
There's no way you can get
around that.
It's in your face 24/seven.
(laughter)
I just keep going.
What is it, mullet?
>> PROBST: At Foa Foa, Russell
had no intention of providing
for his tribe.
>> You know, I eat one papaya
a day.
They lucky if they get a
little bitty piece.
I'm not their daddy.
I'm not gonna bring them
food.
They're not my babies.
We're out here to win a
million dollars.
It's right there in their face.
All they got to do is look up
and it's right there.
It's all over the place.
So I'm gonna just keep
eating, and if I find out that
somebody knows about my spot,
I'm voting them out. (chuckles)
>> What is that?
>> PROBST: But he wasn't the
only castaway dining in secret.
>> Oh, that's good. Mmm.
>> Lookit, let's eat
a little bit.
>> Mmm, this is delicious.
>> Cheers, guys.
>> Oh, my God! Cheers.
>> Nice work.
>> Yeah, baby.
>> Hell, yeah, I'm so glad.
>> Sweet, huh?
>> This is so great.
>> Yeah, the ripe ones
are beautiful.
>> It goes down and then stops.
And it feels so good.
>> Oh!
(laughter)
>> I'm in heaven!
>> I know.
>> No.
>> Okay, good.
>> What papaya?
(laughter)
>> That's what I'm talking
about!
Let's go.
Let's do this.
(sing-songy): I'm not sharing.
>> PROBST: After winning the
first immunity challenge, Galu
took home flint.
>> A big ol' mound full of it.
>> Yeah!
>> Give it a little blow.
No, not from above.
From the side.
>> No, no, no, no, no, hush.
You guys shut up, please.
Don't blow.
Like fireworks, isn't it? Damn.
>> When we were making fire it
was pretty frustrating because
Shambo really wanted to be the
one to make fire.
The problem, is Shambo doesn't
really know how to make fire.
>> There we go, there we go,
there we go, there we go.
>> Now you blow lightly,
very lightly.
>> Just don't let that go out.
Keep it covered.
Keep it covered here.
It's all right, it's all right.
>> Man, I'm exhausted.
>> It's okay.
>> There have been several
times when I just want to go,
"What? Did your mom drop you on
your head?"
Because that is not the correct
way to do it, not even a
smart way to do it.
>> Do you, you want to hit some
flint on here?
>> I would love to take a crack
at it, but I would very much
like to be in charge for the
time I am doing it.
>> Whatever.
Now you're pissing me off.
Okay, let's not have
a conversation.
>> Cool. No problem.
>> I'm serious.
>> Where's that machete?
>> Oh, sorry.
>> Don't be sorry.
Just don't let if happen again.
>> Hey, Dave, be my hero, man.
>> Dude, what are you doing?
There is no wind.
That's why you build a fire pit.
>> Dave looks like he knows what
he's doing.
I have faith that he's gonna
make this happen, so let's
just let it happen.
>> Dave's just a complete and
utter moron.
He won't take assistance or
help from anybody for anything.
Nothing in my life has ever
operated without teamwork, so
it just hit me the wrong way,
you know.
I have to constantly remind
myself, "You're not at home,
"Shannon.
This isn't your family."
>> There we go, there we go,
there we go.
>> I want everybody to back off.
>> Oh, yeah. It's going.
It's igniting. Oh, my gosh.
>> Wait on it.
>> Back off that.
No, it's all good.
It's all good
>> It's going.
Russell, we got this for
you, baby.
>> Shh-shh-shh!
>> Fire, you guys!
>> My awesomeness, it speaks
for itself.
I'm the provider.
I'm the fire maker.
So I am pretty much
bulletproof, I think.
>> Really?
>> I mean if it got down
down to he or I at the end
somewhere and that was the only
ammo I had against him, of
course I'd use it.
>> PROBST: On day five, the
adrenaline surged as the tribes
pushed each other to the limits.
>> You got it, Ashley!
>> PROBST: Erik with
an underhand.
Galu wins reward and immunity!
After another Foa Foa loss,
lessons from Jaison's past came
back to haunt him.
All right, Galu...
>> Before, before you move,
I want to say something.
>> PROBST: Yes.
>> I want to play within the
rules and I want to try to be a
sportsman, but if someone is
gonna try and elbow me, I'm
coming for 'em, and that's the
way it's gonna go down.
So, hey, I'm gonna try to
say the right thing.
Congratulations, Galu, good
job, but I'm coming for John in
the next one.
I'm coming for him.
I had a lot of emotions going
today after that thing was over.
It just brought up a lot of
stuff from the past that have
really been the motivating
factor for why I try to succeed
so much in life.
I don't know who John is, but I
know guys like this, guys who
get ahead by not playing
by the rules.
>> I just got one short, sweet:
that was a beautiful, amazing
competition.
The only thing that I'm really
disheartened about is
I'm coming for you."
Jaison, let's leave the blood
on the battlefield.
Nobody needs to get hurt.
>> Say the same thing to your
teammate over there and then
it'll all be good.
>> Okay, stop.
>> I should not have said what I
said to John, period.
My dad grew up in rural
Mississippi, got kicked off his
land by the Klan, graduated
with honors from Long Beach
State, and got a Ph.D
from Stanford.
And all the while he didn't
complain.
He didn't moan.
He just shut up and he got up
earlier the next day and he went
out and won.
And every time that
say something like that, I feel
like I let him down because
that's not what I'm supposed
to be doing, and I am more
disappointed in myself right
now than anybody else out there.
>> PROBST: Galu, back-to-back
immunity wins.
>> Whoo!
>> I just feel like I have
something to prove,
and I think that's why I came
out here.
I came out here to prove
something.
I need to win, not just survive
or make it to the next round.
I need to win.
>> PROBST: On day nine, Shambo
had accidentally let loose one
of Galu's hard-earned chickens.
(chickens clucking, crowing)
By day 12, as the chicken
continued to elude capture...
...it became a personal quest
for Erik.
>> Chicken.
>> Over there.
(chicken clucking)
>> Is that it?
>> At this point, I think it's
more personal with Erik and the
the chicken.
I think that he has to beat
that chicken.
(clucking)
(squawking)
(Erik grunting)
(chicken squawking)
>> Damn it!
That chicken's fast.
(panting)
Advantage chicken.
At least this time, I didn't
clothesline myself.
(clucking)
(thunder crashing)
>> PROBST: On night 14,
huddling together through the
cold and the rain, Russell
almost spilled the beans about
his personal fortune.
>> This sucks.
(laughter)
I wish I had on rain clothes.
>> So, at this point, would
anything make y'all quit
right now?
I'm really a multimillionaire.
I own an oil company in
Houston, and that's how stupid
these people really are.
They think that I'm some
redneck from the South that
can't do anything.
Well, you know what?
I'm the richest man here.
>> No. What are you gonna talk
about, Russell?
>> It's obviously something if
he won't tell, but hey...
>> I know.
>> Russell seems pretty solid.
He's got that kind of Southern
charm going on, he's got kids.
You want to trust the, like,
kind of Southern family guy
thing, but maybe that's his
his shtick.
>> Does it really look like I'm
a millionaire?
I'm playing all these people
like fools.
There is a difference between
book smarts and common sense
smarts.
It seems like none in my
group has any common sense, not
a one of them.
But it's definitely not gonna
catch up with me here 'cause
I'm tell nobody until the end.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: The next morning,
Mick still had doubts about
Russell's honesty.
>> Boo-yah!
(both laugh)
>> I knew you did, man.
I knew there was something...
>> Really?
Nice, man. Good for you.
>> Mick is a good guy.
If I tell Mick that I have
money, he's gonna think he
can trust me even more.
I mean, if I would have thought
that Mick would say anything
about what I do for a living,
then I wouldn't have told him.
I was living in a trailer check-
by-check five years ago.
>> Russell's a pretty savvy
guy, so it doesn't really
surprise me.
I think we sort of, you know,
bonded a little bit.
I told him what I really
did, too.
And so I think it was kind of a
show of trust on both sides
Because I can be judged based
on, you know, my potential
earning income as well.
You know, physicians still do
pretty well.
We're not murdering it like we
used to.
But could somebody use that
against me?
Absolutely.
But, uh, you know, if it got
down to he or I at the end
somewhere and that was the only
ammo I had against him, of
course I'd use it.
>> We're trying to take you
deep into this game.
>> I resent the fact that you
guys are taking me way into it.
... you guys?
>> Okay, I appreciate that.
>> That's my pride.
The tribe of Galu is going to
take me deep into the game.
Oh, I'm so appreciative.
These people can kiss my ass.
>> PROBST: On day 19
the tribes merged on
the Galu beach.
( cheers and applause )
>> Foa Foa, they think that
they're going to strategize and
make friends.
What's Samoan for "Get the hell
off my island"?
Nobody talks to Shambo, period.
>>Perfect.
>> Let her...
>> PROBST: The original Galu
men agreed to keep the details
from their ally Shambo, but
she wasn't in the mood to be
kept in the dark.
>> What else is new?
>> Uh, I was told not to tell.
Is that going to be okay?
Are you going to be mad at me?
>> I'm not gonna be mad at you
I think it's enough.
I mean, I'm not seven, and
that's how I'm being treated.
>> How could I make you
feel better?
>> (scoffs) Give me a
direct answer.
Make your own decision, Dave,
whatever.
>> Okay. I'd like to burn Shambo
right now just to get her out of
my hair, but she's too valuable
to our alliance so we're gonna
keep her around and just deal
with it, um, even though
I think she's dangerous
because she is unpredictable.
You don't know what she's gonna
do, but the boys assure me we
can control her, so I'm, like,
"All right. Time will tell."
>> It makes people worry
that you will flip out, okay?
>> That's-that's fair.
But you know what?
>> All right? They're, they're
afraid that you're gonna
flip out.
>> I haven't flipped out
I haven't done...
I've been bossy around camp.
I let the chicken go.
I lost the snorkel.
>> We're trying to take you
deep into this game.
We're concerned that you will
accidentally say something, and
I want to you relax and know
that we're taking you way
into this.
And I don't want there to be
any problems.
>> I resent the fact that you
guys are taking me way into it?
You guys?
>> Okay I appreciate that.
>> That's my pride.
>> I apologize.
You're absolutely right.
That was, that was unfair.
>> You know, I'm-I'm nobody's
ninny, or "Shambo, we're gonna
let you be number eight."
... you guys.
>> No, no, no, no.
All right, now watch out.
>> No.
>> I see your feelings, all
right, and I'm trying to help.
>> Dave was, like, "I can tell
"you that we're gonna carry
"you along in this game as long
"as we can, but we can't tell
"you what's going on because you
can't be trusted."
I'm like, "Dude, ... you.
What am I, seven?
I don't need you to bring me
along in the game.
>> Give me a hug. Come on.
>> I'm not in a huggy mood.
>> Fair enough.
All right, I gotta go
get to work.
Are we good?
>> We're good, Dave.
>> All right, mama.
>> Thanks, babe.
>> Yep, good job.
>> The tribe of Galu is going
to take me deep into the game.
Oh, I'm so appreciative.
These people can kiss my ass.
>> PROBST: The next morning as
Shambo licked her wounds, Erik
still had chicken on the brain.
>> In Rocky 2, Rocky wasn't
ready to fight Apollo and win
against Apollo until he was able
to catch that chicken.
(grunts)
Day 20 right now.
Halfway through.
Getting closer to the chicken.
But I don't think I can win
this game and knock Apollo
Creed out until I've caught
that chicken.
(neck cracking)
(chicken clucking)
This isn't the way to
catch this chicken.
You got to be smarter than
the chicken, not stronger than
the chicken.
I'm gonna take the
fishing net.
I'm gonna put it on four
different branches, lock them
down, lift the middle up, tie
it to a branch up top, put some
fishing line on that, and it
will be a giant, like, tent.
Put some coconuts, some trash,
some bugs as kind of like bait.
All right, you locked in?
>> Yup.
>> All right, let go.
>> Presumably, the chicken goes
under it, and all he has
to do is go stand next
to those torches, cut a
line, and the thing drops.
>> PROBST: With Erik out
crabbing, it was Shambo
to the rescue.
>> Chicken!
(chicken clucking)
(chicken squawking)
>> I got the chicken!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
>> All right, you got him?
>> Don't you kill my chicken.
>> Nicely done.
>> Erik! Erik!
(chicken squawking)
>> I know. You're okay.
(cheers and applause )
>> Oh!
>> My little noogie chicken.
That's the most comforting
feeling that I've had in
probably three weeks was to hold
that little devastated chicken
in my arm, and it needed me and
I needed it, and it was, it was
a good moment.
(clucking)
Hey! Meow!
You be nice!
The chicken has returned home,
and the mighty hunter Erik has,
uh...
He's validated.
>> We got the chicken!
>> You got the chicken?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Erik returned home
to great news.
>> I'm so happy!
>> Oh...
>> Ah!
Yes!
Finally, the trap I set, devised
worked like a charm, and now
that chicken that I stalked,
that in return mocked me for
ten, 12 days-- finally, back
where it belongs in that coop.
>> Yeah, I got to admit, I had
my doubts on the trap, but...
>> Dude!
>> There's two chickens in the
freaking coop again, bro.
>> PROBST: Later that night,
Russell was up to his old tricks
with his new tribe.
(clucking)
>> You know, it's time for me to
create the chaos.
I'm in a bind right now, so I
have to get everybody else at
each other's throat.
I decided to open the hatch so
the chickens could get out,
because when they're gone
tomorrow, all hell's gonna break
loose.
It's gonna cause chaos once
again.
Erik was so excited.
"They got the chicken."
(Russell laughs)
He was so excited.
Let's see how he feels when they
lose two chickens.
You know, I want to have a
little bit of fun tonight, so I
get up, and I put the idol
around my neck.
I start looking at everybody
sleeping.
Uh, that's what I do.
I live on the edge.
All of a sudden, I see Dave's
up.
I say, "Oh, this is great."
I'm gonna go by Dave, talk to
him.
You better be cocky in this
game, because if you're not,
then you're gone.
>> Oh, no.
>> You know what?
'Cause, I, uh...
My impression of Foa Foa is that
they're tired, and they're
scared, and they're holding
together now, but I don't really
care, 'cause we're gonna be able
to knock them off.
Who gives a crap.
>> I thought it was funny that
Dave was sitting there talking
to me, and the idol's sitting
right there.
All he's got to do is look at
it, but he never did.
None of them are thinking really
the game.
They're thinking, get rid of
Foa Foa.
They think they have numbers.
They think that, uh, they're
just gonna weed us out one
at a time.
It's not gonna happen.
>> PROBST: Facing Tribal Council
as a newly merged tribe, Erik's
head was suddenly on the
chopping block.
>> Everyone's on board?
>> PROBST: And Brett was the
last to know.
>> Hey Brett, Brett?
>> Uh-oh.
>> They say... They say
everybody's on board with Erik.
>> Shh!
>> I'll be completely honest,
'cause you are the people that I
trust.
>> Yes.
>> I know that...
I hon-honestly don't...
>> Yes?
>> I think we should at least
give it some time to discuss.
>> No, I think it's...
>> No. I don't... Jais...
We don't... It's...
>> Is this ... done or what?
>> Yes. Shh.
>> We can get him out next time.
Jaison... Just...
>> Here he comes.
>> Okay.
>> All right.
>> Erik is actually someone that
I see myself gonna the end of
the game with, and so for my
alliances essentially saying
they all want to vote out Erik,
when he wasn't even discussed at
all throughout the day, just
baffles me.
I don't understand why.
>> Because...
>> Because every...
>> There's...
>> All of sudden, literally,
every single person that you
trust here, besides Erik, every
single person...
>> ...but apparently, it's
already done, and you got to
get comfortable quick, because
every single person is voting
for Erik, so you've got to get
on the train, because it's
already left the station.
>> Yup.
>> And I'm the same way you
were.
>> So he's totally not, dude.
He's banned, dude.
He's cancer.
We got to dump him now.
>> It's already done.
>> I understand.
I got 30 seconds with Dave.
>> Apparently, people have made
up their minds, but...
>> Yeah.
>> ...I have not seen reason.
>> Yeah, yeah. No, I understand.
>> Obviously, the decision's
already been made, and, you
know, there's not a lot I can
do, and so my plan now is
basically, just fly under the
radar for the time being, and I
think that that will carry me
through for a while, and then,
um, I'll need to step it up
and-and start, you know, making
a few decisions.
>> Welcome to Survivor.
>> PROBST: Reluctantly, Brett
followed his Galu alliance and
helped blindside one of their
own.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa, and the first
member of our jury-- Erik.
>> The vote tonight, I think,
will shape the rest of the game
completely, and I hope that
doesn't screw up my entire game.
>> PROBST: Erik, the tribe has
spoken.
>> (voice breaking): I knew at
some point I was just gonna
break down bawling.
>> Don't work yourself up into
something that's not there.
>> Laura and I did not have a
heart-to-heart conversation in
her little reach out and touch
me superficial bull...
Don't make me throw up on your
face.
>> PROBST: By day 23, the
emotional burden of the game
took its toll on Shambo.
And home was all she could
think about.
>> I'm Irish.
I'm not supposed to be in the
sun.
>> How many of you are there?
>> Nine kids.
My...
>> Your brother passed away,
right?
>> My brother Terry died of
meningitis when he was about
three months old.
And then my sister Donna died of
cancer the day before her 27th
birthday.
>> That's sad.
>> Well, they're better off.
>> Was she older or younger was
she?
She was older?
>> Donna was older.
She went through radiation and
chemotherapy for a long time
and then they told her that she
was fine and there was no
traces of cancer.
She was a newlywed when the
cancer was found.
>> Oh, you're kidding.
>> She'd only been married,
like, 18 months.
And then she went in for a scan
and they said it was full-blown
back.
>> Oh.
Oh, Shammy.
>> I knew at some point I was
just going to break down
bawling.
>> She's really proud of you,
Sham.
Guarantee you that one thing.
How old were you?
>> I was 23.
I was stationed in Okinawa, and
I remember my staff sergeant
saying, "Corporal Waters go
back to the barracks, you got
an emergency phone call from
the Red Cross."
And I just started bawling.
I was like God dang it.
Who died?
Because I didn't know.
>> Come on.
Where's our sunshine?
>> Laura and I did not have a
heart-to-heart conversation.
Laura invaded a private moment
that I was having on the beach
where I was really homesick.
I was missing my family, and I
started think thinking about my
sister that passed away over 20
years ago.
I was just, I was pretty much
broken down and sad, and she
wanted to play buddy-buddy
with me.
And her little "reach out and
touch me" superficial bull...
>> Be thankful that you're here.
We have 20 more days.
>> I feel like the girls out
here are out to get me.
>> Well I think you're a lot--
you're self-paranoid, too.
I think the more paranoid you
are, the worse it gets.
>> I don't think I'm paranoid,
though, Lolo, I don't.
>> I'm telling you, you are.
Don't work yourself up into
something that's not there.
>> I can't stand Laura.
I want no conversations with
her.
You don't even like me, and you
want to sit here and pretend
like you're befriending me.
It's just, like don't make me
throw up on your face.
>> PROBST: On day 27, Russell
believed he had it all under
control, so he began to make
moves to ensure his safety
further in the game.
>> I'm in control of this game.
Everything has worked for me so
far.
I set up my alliance so strong,
my four people, including me,
they come up to me.
They tell me everything.
And you have to be able to
outwit them, even if it's your
best alliance.
You have to be able to outwit
them, too.
They're going to turn on you,
Foa Foa.
Believe it when I say it.
I'm the one that's going to
take you.
They'll get rid of you.
Yeah.
Who do you think's going to be
gone first?
>> It feels really good to be
aligned with Russell.
I mean, he is the most powerful
player in this game.
He knows that whatever he votes,
I vote, too.
So really he's got two votes no
matter what, any way he wants
to play it.
It may, you know, mess me up in
the end, but I've made it this
far, so, you know, I'm just
going to trust him, and we'll go
with it, and I'm hoping that
I'll be in the final two.
>> Now, I want to you promise me
one thing I'll never ask you
again.
>> Okay.
>> When it comes down to brass
knuckles, and it's just me and
you and somebody else, you have
to swear to me you ain't going
to think that I'm going to beat
you because I played the game
better and vote me off.
Swear on Mick.
You're going to start thinking.
That's a lot of money.
Your brain's going to start
working.
>> It's... You know what?
It's not worth the money to me
to lose my integrity out here.
If I give you my word, I give
you my word, and that's the
bottom line.
>> All right.
You know, it all comes to a head
sooner or later.
>> For sure, I agree.
>> I would think my best partner
out here would be Natalie.
You see, Natalie is my ticket to
get rid of both Jaison and Mick.
So she can go pretty far in this
game with me, maybe all the way
to the final two.
'Cause who better to take?
There's no way she can beat me
in votes.
She followed and did everything
I told her to do.
She wouldn't even know how to
talk.
She might even say, "Oh, he's
right.
Give it all to him."
You know, she's so sweet, I love
it.
>> PROBST: With Kelly voted out,
the original Galu members were
grasping at anything to stop
their freefall.
>> I just wish there was a way
that Kelly were here so we could
keep Galu together.
>> Well, it's not reality.
>> I know. I know, I know.
>> That's not where we find
ourselves.
>> The game freaking changes.
>> Well, the game changes every
day, but...
>> Yeah.
>> Sit down, Mon.
>> I feel like from my best
position right now, the best
thing is to just wait it out and
stick with Galu.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Is there a Galu since Erik
got blindsided, to you,
personally, in the real freaking
world to be true?
>> I just don't know that I can
trust anybody from Foa Foa...
>> Listen to me.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Don't lower your brows like I
just attacked you.
Drop the bull about Galu
loyalty, 'cause there is none.
It's Puff the Magic Freaking
Dragon, okay?
>> But why, Shambo?
>> That's a pipe dream.
>> Why?
Why does it have to be that way?
>> Because you guys chose to
vote for Galu before Foa Foa,
and it broke.
>> But it was different.
>> It's...
>> He was turning his back...
>> It always is.
>> ...on Galu.
>> It always is because it's
Survivor, yes?
>> That was different, though.
>> It doesn't matter who it was
or why it was.
>> Right.
>> Purple is broken.
Erik helped us win every single
solitary challenge that we won.
He was...
>> Because it helped himself.
He was fake purple.
>> Then Kelly's fake purple for
having a knife in my back.
And why was there conversations
had, lead by Laura, to get rid
of Shambo?
That's fake purple.
So don't talk to me about fake
purple.
Purple is fake.
There is no fake, there is no
real.
It's Survivor.
>> Yeah.
(thunder rumbling)
>> PROBST: That night in Tribal
Council, the remaining Foa Foa
tribe and Shambo declared
victory.
Ninth person voted out and the
third member of our jury, Laura.
>> Oh, my gosh.
The day of reckoning has come.
Laura is gone.
Now, it's an individual game.
And I'm not sure what's going
to happen.
>> PROBST: Nine castaways are
left.
>> I'm here to win the million
dollars for myself.
>> PROBST: As the stakes get
higher...
I hope you think it was worth
it.
>> ALL: Oh!
>> PROBST: ...which alliances
will hold true?
>> Russell is Russell, so we got
to watch out.
>> Why would you do something
stupid like that?
>> I did not... I didn't do
that!
>> PROBST: What sacrifices will
the castaways be forced to make?
>> If this goes bad, I mean, I
owe you big time.
>> PROBST: Can old Galu reunite
its force?
>> The writing's on the wall.
>> PROBST: And can anyone stop
Russell?
>> I'm going to write a book on
how to win Survivor.
>> PROBST: Join us next week as
the adventure continues.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor-- Russell and John
make a move.
>> PROBST: So everybody needs an
edge.
This is a significant advantage
in the next immunity challenge.
And Shambo thinks she has a
psychic vision.
>> I dreamed some really crazy
things.
I think that's God's divine
intervention at work.
I had a dream last night we
voted Dave off.
>> ♪ It's the eye of the tiger
It's the thrill of the fight
♪ Rising up to the challenge
Of our rival
♪ It's the last known survivor
At the end of the night
♪ Da-da, da, da-da, da
Da-da, da... ♪
(laughing)