>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor...
Here in Samoa, there are two
tribes going in two different
directions.
For the purple tribe, Galu, it's
sunshine and rainbows.
>> ♪ Coco rico
In my belly... ♪
>> PROBST: They've won both
immunity challenges, and
everyone is happy.
(laughter)
Everyone except Shambo.
>> The way that the rest of
the tribe does things is way
different than the way that I do
things, and it's very
frustrating.
>> PROBST: Losing has frustrated
everyone on Foa Foa...
everyone except Russell.
>> I didn't come here to work.
I came here to play.
>> PROBST: Russell is the first
person in Survivor history to
find a hidden immunity idol
without any clues.
>> Boo-yah.
>> PROBST: He's figured out how
to manipulate the others into
doing his bidding.
>> They can be my little
puppets.
They'll run when I tell 'em to
run, they'll walk when I tell
'em to walk.
And when I'm finished with them,
I'll just throw 'em in the
trash.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, Ben put
people on edge without even
trying.
(Ben babbling gibberish)
He got kicked out of a
challenge...
>> PROBST: Stop!
First time in the history of
Survivor.
Take a spot here-- you're done.
...kept everyone up all night...
...and lashed out at a visitor
from the other tribe.
>> If I was a girl, I would slap
you, is what I would do.
Ghetto trash, plain and simple.
>> PROBST: Ben's actions put a
target on his back.
>> We got a loss because he got
thrown out of the challenge
yesterday.
Ben would be the right choice to
kick out-- he's crazy.
>> PROBST: But Russell wanted
Betsy out, because Betsy didn't
trust him.
>> Why didn't you trust me from
the beginning?
You're gonna look back on this
and regret it.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Russell got his way.
Ben was spared, and Betsy was
voted out.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I did a lot of thinking last
night.
What have you been thinking?
>> I've been thinking Ben's got
to be the next to go.
>> Tell me why, is that for
personal reasons?
>> The guy's mean.
>> I agree with you.
>> I want him out.
>> You see how he laid into her?
I mean, it wasn't just an
argument.
It got really personal and, I
think, inappropriate.
>> "Ghetto trash."
That's not necessary.
>> Totally. Like, that's
terrible.
At the last Tribal Council, Ben
was this close from saying
something to Yasmin that
would've made me fly over a
stool and say... and not even
say but, you know, put him down.
We voted off Betsy, but at this
point, Ben is a mental plague on
our tribe.
>> Ashley.
How you feel?
>> I feel good.
>> How you feel about last
night?
>> It's always brutal, but it
was the... I mean, it was the
majority, it was the plan, so...
>> Do you have any in mind who
you would want to...?
>> Gosh.
>> Nobody here's playing the
game.
Nobody is playing the game but
me, on my tribe.
Not one person-- it's crazy.
>> I think we should definitely
see how today goes before we
start discussing...
>> Well, today's just a reward,
I hope.
>> Yeah, I don't know what today
is.
>> I don't know, this might be
the worst group in history, and
I might be the best.
I'm gonna have them all under
control like zombies walking
around. Mmm...
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
>> Did you put a ton in or just
enough to cover the top a little
bit?
>> If that doesn't get it
started, I don't know what the
hell will.
>> Just... let me just show you
one time.
Hold it really, really tight...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...and try to push that spark
into there.
You want to try?
>> Yeah.
>> Just doing that, though,
you're gonna destroy the flint.
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah.
We're almost out of flint,
'cause these people don't know
what they're doing.
I'm the only one that knows how
to start the fire.
I think a lot of these people
out here, they're not used to
being out in the woods.
Kind of pansies and...
Mick's not an outdoorsy guy like
myself.
I wasn't surprised he didn't
know how to do it.
I tried to show him and give him
a few tips.
Didn't really help.
>> It's usually a little bit
easier than this, yeah?
>> Not with a flint like that.
>> Really?
>> Want me to try for a sec?
>> Yeah.
>> Without my help, these people
will die.
I save the day once again.
>> Oh, you got it going?
>> Yeah.
>> Nice.
>> I started the fire this
morning.
Mick was trying to.
He was having a lot of
trouble with it.
It's a lot of technique, it's
a lot of strength.
Like, not to be chauvinistic,
not to put you girls down-- you
won't be able to start the fire
with the flint.
The way it's worn down, it's,
like, flat?
>> Yeah.
>> If you just try, like, it's
gonna be, like, you're just
gonna waste it.
So I wouldn't even... I wouldn't
even attempt to.
I'm not just saying that.
You're hands aren't big enough--
you can't grip the machete and
get down and do it.
>> Ben is trying to tell
everybody they can't survive
without Ben.
Which, hey, I applaud it.
You're trying to save yourself.
But that's not how you do it.
>> Ben, did you sleep last
night?
>> First time in seven days.
Did you poop yet?
>> No.
>> I pooped this morning, and it
was, like, the biggest poop, I
think, in my life.
>> Ew.
>> You see, as long as Ben keeps
his crazy rantics going on, his
ass is gonna be on the line.
>> You want to bite me?
You want something to bite on?
I got something for you, buddy.
>> I got to keep Ben here a
little bit longer, 'cause he's
good for the challenges, and
he's the strongest guy around
the camp.
So I'm gonna have to debate
which baby I'm gonna have to
send home next.
>> Lizard, anybody?
♪ ♪
>> Exhale out slowly through the
nose.
>> You got it.
>> Again. Nice strident back,
all the way up.
Breath in through the nose.
Hold it in.
Right now we're winning.
We're feeling good.
There's great morale.
We're working hard.
We're all pitching in at camp.
We're all doing stuff.
Exhale out.
So we don't have to always be
in game mode, and that's a huge,
huge advantage that we have over
Foa Foa.
And relax.
>> Are you frickin' kidding me?
We got four people doing yoga
this morning?
I'm kind of alienated from my
tribe, 'cause I'm not in the
90210 clique.
>> We're gonna do this slow two
more times, then we're gonna put
it in rhythm.
>> I'm not doing the warm and
fuzzy, I'm doing the Rambo
Shambo provider role out here.
>> Feet up at an angle.
>> Do we have water? No.
Do we have food? No.
Do we have firewood? No.
Screw yoga, man.
>> So what I'm figuring is,
she's becoming a threat to us.
So, uh, one thing I do know for
a fact is she was trying to get
rid of you.
>> Oh, man.
>> "Got to get rid of Ben.
Got to get rid of Ben."
So just don't tell her nothin'.
We're gonna sneak her.
We're gonna tell her whoever,
and then we're gonna all vote
for her.
The reason I told Ben about
Ashley gunning for him is 'cause
right now I think I need Ben.
So every person that tries to
get rid of him, I'm gonna get
rid of them.
I don't want her to start
talking, "Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben,
Ben."
>> Nobody listens to her anyway.
>> Yeah. So, you know, just keep
it to where we can blindside
her.
>> Cool.
>> All right, man.
I'm telling you, you plant that
little seed in their head, in
their little brain, and then it
grows, and it's called a
"Russell seed."
It takes over their whole mind.
So that makes it easy for me to
manipulate every single one of
them.
>> You know what?
Last night you stabbed me in the
back.
>> I did nothing wrong.
I was playing the game.
>> You didn't come to me when
you heard something about me, at
all.
>> Because I didn't think I
needed to at that exact moment.
>> You know what?
That's the easiest thing, to
come and say, "Hey, you know
what, everybody's talking about
you."
I had to find out from somebody
else.
>> Who'd you find out from?
>> It wasn't Russell, that's all
I'm saying.
And I don't trust you, so I'm
not gonna say anything else.
That's not surprising.
>> When people fight, I love
that.
How can they not even think it
was me, you know?
These people are just idiots.
It is shocking that these people
trust me so much.
I mean, they really do.
Everybody here trusts me.
>> No, that's not true.
>> I know.
>> I can promise you that's not
true.
>> No, I know.
You gonna say something to him?
I did not say that. I didn't.
>> You know what I told him, I
was, like, you know what, I'm
not gonna fight with you.
>> I've never been so confused
in my entire life.
Yesterday Ben's name got thrown
around by everyone, and
apparently, someone said that I
was the one that brought it up,
so I do not feel safe.
I want to know who told him.
>> Brett's back, Monica's back.
>> Tree mail!
>> I love presents.
>> Is everyone here?
>> Oh, there's a... like, a bag.
>> I know.
>> I like the feel, though.
>> You see over here?
I just want to go over here.
>> Like the feel.
That's a pillowcase right there.
>> Oh!
(indistinct chatter)
>> You ready?
>> All right, go ahead.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> "If you can't run or swim or
lift or carry, then you'd
better be damn smart.
Only one tribe stays home safe
and comfy while the loser shall
depart."
>> Wow.
>> Bathing suits!
>> Yeah, dude.
>> Yay!
(cheering)
>> All right, so...
>> Oh.
>> Yay!
>> Yes.
>> So we got tree mail today.
It came with this nice comfy
little dry sack of clothing
which most of us guessed would
be swimsuits.
I'm putting this right on right
now!
So now, here it is.
And it feels awesome and dry
and soft and fabulous.
Oh, yay!
I can't even tell you how
amazing this feels.
>> Shambo, how you feeling?
>> Ready to rock 'n' roll, man.
I got my jogger bra on.
(laughs)
>> I just did it the wrong way.
>> 'Cause you're the blonde.
>> Of course.
(laughter)
Of course.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Galu getting your first look at
the new Foa Foa tribe.
Betsy voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
You'll also notice that Mike
Borassi is gone from the game.
Medical's decision, not his.
Nonetheless, he is gone.
Foa Foa is now down to seven.
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yup.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
I will take back the immunity
idol.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, two
members of each tribe will swim
out to retrieve a crate.
The section between the four
flags is a battle zone where a
defender from the other tribe
will be waiting to try to slow
you down.
It will get physical.
Once both swimmers get through
the zone, you're free to
retrieve your crate.
Once you have your crate back
to the mat, the next two go.
Once you've collected all four
crates, you must stack them so
that there are no repeating
colors on any side.
First tribe to get it right
wins a lot.
Immunity.
If you have immunity, you do
not go to Tribal Council.
You cannot be voted out of this
game.
In addition, the winning tribe
wins reward.
A lot of comfort.
>> Oh!
>> Yay!
>> It's a hammock!
>> PROBST: Because this
challenge runs six on six, both
tribes are sitting people out.
Foa Foa, you're sitting out one
man.
>> Russell.
>> PROBST: All right.
Russell's going to sit out for
Foa Foa.
Galu, you're sitting out four
people-- two men, two women.
>> Shambo, Yasmin for the two
girls.
Erik and Brett for the two guys.
>> PROBST: All right, sit-outs
take your spot.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize, we'll get started.
First round, Liz and Natalie
for Foa Foa.
Monica and Laura for Galu.
Defenders-- Kelly for Galu,
Ashley for Foa Foa.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Ashley takes down
Monica.
Laura getting in on it.
(overlapping shouting)
>> Come on, Laura!
>> PROBST: Liz and Natalie
getting tied up from Kelly.
She's got both of them.
Yeah, Kelly!
Laura is dragging Ashley.
Literally dragging her out of
the battle zone.
You're both free! Go!
Both of you have to be at the
crate!
>> Ashley!
>> PROBST: Liz is now dragging
her tribe mate out of the
battle zone.
You're free. Go!
>> Go! Go! Go! Go!
>> Come on, ladies!
>> PROBST: Monica and Laura
heading back with that first
crate for Galu.
Natalie and Liz need to make up
some time.
Liz and Natalie at that first
crate.
Monica and Laura are back.
John and Dave heading out on
the course, Ben defending
against John and Dave.
(indistinct shouting)
Both guys elude Ben!
You're clear!
(cheering)
Natalie and Liz back with that
first crate.
Mick and Jaison taking on
Russell.
Russell takes down Mick.
Ben is now on Russell.
Jaison getting in on it.
(grunting)
(indistinct chatter & shouting)
Mick gets free!
Jaison is free.
John and Dave heading back with
that second crate for Galu and
a big, big lead.
>> Come on in there.
>> Nice job, nice job!
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: Monica and Laura now
back out.
Ashley trying to defend again.
Ashley takes down Monica hard
in the water.
(cheering)
Ashley has Laura's leg.
Mick and Jaison back with the
second crate for Foa Foa.
Liz and Natalie back out on the
course.
(indistinct shouting)
Kelly unstoppable.
Liz once again pulling her
tribe mates across.
You're free.
Monica and Laura heading back
with that third crate for Galu.
(indistinct shouting)
Natalie and Liz at that third
crate for Foa Foa.
They're heading back.
(overlapping chatter)
Go!
Galu heading out for their
fourth and final crate.
Russell now deflecting against
Ben.
>> Whoa.
>> PROBST: John taunts Ben, and
he's free.
They're both free of Ben.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Natalie and Liz now
back with that third crate.
Jaison and Mick now heading
out, looking for their fourth
and final crate.
Ben has Russell, takes him
down, and that's it.
Mick and Jaison are free.
John and Dave at that fourth
crate heading back for Galu.
Mick and Jaison have their
fourth and final crate.
They're heading back.
John and Dave turning on the
afterburners now, and they're
running it in.
Start untying the crates.
Come on with the knots.
Mick and Jaison now running it
up.
>> All right, guys.
>> PROBST: Start untying.
>> Let's go, Galu!
>> PROBST: Galu already starting
to work on their puzzle.
They have a big lead after the
swim.
Foa Foa trying to catch up.
Each side of this puzzle must
have four different colors.
>> Rotate this one.
>> PROBST: If you have two of
the same color on any side, it
is wrong.
(overlapping chatter)
Foa Foa thinks they have it.
Rotate it.
Green, red, blue, green. No!
>> Keep going!
>> PROBST: You've got a
repeating color.
Keep working.
>> Bring up the bottom of this
one.
>> Right here.
>> Green!
>> This is the one.
>> Green over here!
Red...
>> PROBST: Galu thinks they have
it.
Rotate it.
Green, blue, purple, red.
Purple, red, green, blue.
Last side-- blue, green, purple,
red.
Galu wins immunity and reward!
(cheering)
>> Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
(whooping)
>> PROBST: Galu, for the third
straight time, immunity is
yours.
(applause)
Once again, Galu, safe from
Tribal Council.
Nobody going home on this tribe.
In addition, huge reward.
Along with that, a decision for
your leader.
Russell, come on up here.
So here's the deal.
This is what you won-- comfort.
If you want, as leader, you can
trade it for this.
>> Oh, there's a tarp.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: You have comfort, or
you have function.
Five seconds to decide.
>> Comfort.
>> PROBST: All right, right over
here.
(applause, cheers and whooping)
>> PROBST: Galu, any debate for
you about which would have made
more sense for the tribe?
>> We've been fine in food.
We're fine.
We need comfort.
We want to lay our heads down.
That's it.
That's the way to go.
>> And that's why I made the
decision, Jeff.
I am a function guy, but they
are a comfort group right now,
so I got to go with the group.
>> PROBST: Okay.
>> But there was that split
second, I was like, "Towels?
What the hell do we need towels
for?
There's no showers out here."
I know the guys are going to be
all over me, but at the end of
the day, if I make the women
happy, we're going to be happy.
(laughing)
(whooping)
>> Russell took the comfort.
Danger Dave here would have
said, "Geez, let me think about
this for zero seconds.
I'll take the function."
But it was the chief's choice.
We were not allowed to make the
decision.
>> PROBST: All right, Russell,
you have one other decision to
make now.
You're sending one person from
your tribe over to Foa Foa.
Once again, a chance for
somebody to observe, sit in on
Tribal Council.
Who are you going to send?
>> Shambo.
>> PROBST: Shambo, you're going
over to the other side.
How do you feel about that?
>> I'm good.
>> PROBST: Come over here.
This is for you.
It says, "Open in private."
Go join Foa Foa.
Shambo will stay with you
through Tribal Council, and then
return back to her own camp.
All right, Galu, grab your
stuff, get your reward, head
out.
>> Ashley stabbed me in the
back the other day, so Ashley
is gonna get the snip.
>> You're Mick?
>> Yeah, hi.
>> we call you "Mc-Dreamy."
>> Good to have you.
>> Jaison?
>> Jaison.
>> What's up, brother?
>> How you doing, Shambo?
>> I'm Shannon.
>> I'm Liz.
>> You are one tough,
beast-like competitor.
Come here.
>> I can't believe...
>> Oh, my God, girl.
>> At the end of the challenge,
the winning tribe got to pick
someone to come over to our
tribe, so Russell chose Shambo.
A totally different vibe than
Yasmin.
I mean, she's just-- we'd like
to adopt her.
I mean, she's just such great
energy.
She's just good people.
>> Ashley.
>> Hi, smiley girl, how are you?
>> Good.
>> So nice to finally talk
to you.
>> I know.
>> One of my main objectives in
this game was to create
interpersonal relationships as
soon as possible.
So when Russell picked me to
go, I was tickled pink to head
over and check out Foa Foa.
>> Shambo, I'm Ben.
>> Big Benjamin, what's going
on, beefcake?
>> Nothing much.
>> Those bright eyes smiling at
everybody all the time.
There was a lot of chitter-chat.
I shared with them, they shared
with me.
And, it's funny, people here
are closer to my own age, they
get me, I get them.
I feel like I have more in
common with this tribe than
people on my tribe.
>> They're all younger.
>> They're like 90210.
I'm hanging out with 90210 and
it's absolutely mind-boggling.
I don't think it's like life or
death to, say, get everybody
together in the morning and go,
"Okay, you guys, this is what we
need to accomplish, and as soon
as we get it done, the day is
yours."
>> Yeah, we get crab...
>> 90210 wanted to do yoga this
morning instead of get water.
>> Yoga?
>> Really?
>> We don't have the luxury of
doing yoga.
We're like up the...
>> I'm sorry, baby.
I'm not in the Survivor game
to play yoga, okay?
>> Of course she's here for a
reason, so she's here to find
the immunity idol, I presume,
and to get information to go
back to her tribe which she
claims she's not super tight
with.
But you always have to assume
someone's lying, always.
>> You guys appreciate me for
the woman I am.
>> Yeah!
>> I love you, Shannon.
>> Yoga.
>> When I got the note from Jeff
I thought it was hidden
immunity idol clues, and I was
exactly right.
"If you think you need
protection and would like
immunity, look here at Foa Foa
and bark up the right tree.
Clue 2: Within sight of the
fire and close to the ground,
seek the root of the problem
and salvation will be found."
Wow.
I am very excited.
There's a hidden immunity idol
at the Foa Foa camp.
My tribe is probably going to
try to vote me out sooner or
later anyway.
So this totally rocks.
>> Now Shambo has the second
note, but I have the immunity
idol without any letters or
anything.
I just used my brilliant brain
to figure out where it was.
I'm running this whole show
right now.
I'm the boss.
That was, like, such a great...
>> We have blankets!
>> So, to be honest my natural
inclination today was to take
that camping stuff.
But here's the deal-- I'm the
type of man that believes that
you're supposed to take care of
your women, all right?
I've got a wife and a daughter.
They're not here.
You guys are, all right?
Right now, you guys are part of
my women.
I got to take care of you,
all right?
So, guys, I wanted you to
know that.
So we've got a little bit of
work to do.
Hopefully we can get some
good food...
>> We'll get the bed fixed.
How's that?
>> That sounds good.
>> After we arrived back at
camp with our comfort items
there was a little monologue
given by Russell that I think
to him he sort of felt, like,
obliged to justify his decision.
>> We're having a bed.
>> For crying out loud, how
comfortable are four pillows,
three beach towels and two
woven palm frond mats going to
make you?
You're still going to be
uncomfortable.
>> How are those mats feeling?
>> Perfect.
>> Come lay down here with me.
>> Russell did not take the
tarp and I think that was a bad
move.
I would have sacrificed
everything on that comfort item
list for the tarp.
Because maybe it won't rain for
39 days.
Maybe I'm wrong.
But the day it does rain over
here, every single one of those
comfort luxury items are going
to be soaked and all of a
sudden not so comfortable.
These girls here think that
this is like Club Med.
It's not Club Med.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> You did so good out there.
>> You did.
>> I'm so proud of you.
>> Yeah.
I mean, it's like this.
If it's not, then I'm leaving.
So everybody can make a
decision.
I'm just saying.
Like I am going to put it out
there like that.
That is my ultimatum.
>> That's fine.
>> I'm trying to circulate it
that I might just walk away if
Ben is here after Tribal
Council.
You know, I have no intention
of quitting whatsoever, but I'm
willing to do just about
anything to get rid of that guy
right now.
It's the racist comments.
I won't stand here and tolerate
that.
I just won't.
>> Natalie, if I get kicked out
I'm leaving you my sweater and
my tennis shoes, okay?
>> Jaison is like it's either
me or him.
>> No, it's either me or him?
>> No, no, no.
>> I don't know what to think
anymore.
No one understands unless their
name gets brought up.
Ben has some personal thing
against me.
And I'm trying as much as
possible to not have me
eliminated.
But it's hard.
>> Ashley's going home.
>> And who else is on board
with that?
You?
Yeah.
I'm saying...
>> All right.
>> So Russell and Liz are
adamant about voting Ashley
out, but that worries me
because I am definitely loyal
to Jaison.
>> Yeah, yeah.
Definitely.
>> I like Jaison.
Even though, man, he's just
not...
His mind's getting messed up.
>> I know.
>> He's getting broke down.
>> He really lets this stuff
get to him.
But I just want you to know,
Russell, that, you know, I think
you have a good enough vibe from
me already that I'm a
trustworthy guy, and I'll go by
my word, and I will.
And if that's my downfall, then
so be it.
You know, I want to win.
I'm here to win, too--
>> Then give me your word you
won't vote for me and we'll let
Ben go next.
>> All right.
After Ashley?
>> After Ashley.
>> Look me in the eye.
>> You've got my word.
>> All right, done and done.
>> I want Mick to trust me, and
I want him to know how
important it is that we stick
together and we can make this
work.
So, I'm going to let him know
about the hidden immunity idol.
The immunity idol is a powerful
tool, and it is a tool to where
this person would say, well,
this guy must really trust me.
>> That's some brilliance on
your part.
>> My alliance with Mick is
solid.
So that's just another vote for
me to get Ashley out.
It's simple.
I was born for this.
This is what God made me for.
>> Good job, buddy.
You want to start stripping
them?
You know how to do that?
I'm going to show you guys
lickety-split.
Get it like this.
Go.
Okay?
And then get them like this.
And then wrap them.
And then take the ends, tie it
around, tuck it in, and you
have a little poofy torch.
>> Sweet.
>> Okay?
>> All right.
>> Just like that.
I've been hooking it up and
cooking it up at camp today,
taught them a few new tricks
that they didn't know.
So, you know, trying to be
helpful and make good
relationships with these people.
But I need to start looking for
hidden immunity idol.
I'm going to do a little recon
mission and we'll see what we
can come up with.
Look at all this good
firewood, Liz.
>> Oh.
>> Holy cow!
Oh, dude!
>> I love Shambo.
I wish she were over here.
She is so nice, and she's
bringing a real good energy
to us.
>> Oh, my word, for sure.
>> I can't believe no one's
doing anything at their camp.
>> It's amazing.
Who has time to do yoga on the
beach?
>> It's ridiculous.
>> My sentiments exactly.
>> I noticed the girls are
talking a little more, and I
will regret not sending Ashley
home because there's no way she
ain't going to try to get that
all-girl thing or something.
We got to put a squash on that
and we got this game under
control.
That's the plan, dude.
I think we got to get rid
of her.
I want to get rid of Ashley.
>> What's the problem voting
Ben off tonight?
>> I'm on the fence with Ben
right now.
>> Why?
>> 'Cause I know that what if
we do a challenge?
Is he a strong player?
>> No.
>> You don't think he's
stronger than...?
>> Okay, let's think about the
numbers, then.
>> I don't like that.
>> I don't really like that,
either.
>> They will gang up on us.
Don't believe they won't.
That's the whole thing.
That's what I do not like.
>> Your only concern is the
girls voting us three on three?
I'm not worried about that.
Those girls are so weak it
would be suicide if they tried
to pick us off one by one.
>> And then we'll get rid
of Ben.
I don't want them to have
numbers.
You know, right now, it's just
not-- and I know you hate it--.
>> I know, man.
>> I'm making my peace at this
Tribal Council.
That's the way it's going down.
If you guys want to have
discord in the camp because of
the guy who does nothing in
challenges and provides very
little at camp then you go
right ahead.
And if you leave him here,
that's going to be a rough
night tonight.
That's going to be a rough day
tomorrow.
That's going to be a rough
night the next night.
>> I want to keep Ben around,
but everybody's saying how he's
a poison and this and that.
So it's becoming-- I don't want
them not to trust me.
So it's like... man.
>> PROBST: Shambo, go ahead and
have a seat.
Shambo is just here to observe
tonight, not participate in any
other way.
Jaison, what was it like having
a visitor?
Shambo's been with you guys for
the last day and a half.
>> I think Shambo's amazing,
you know?
I would love to propose a trade
with Galu and trade somebody
for Shambo, specifically Ben,
frankly.
You know, she's a positive
force in camp while he is an
incredibly negative force.
So she's amazing.
I love her.
She's great.
>> PROBST: Ben, first you vote
out Marisa because she's a
negative force.
Last Tribal Council you vote
out Betsy because she's on the
outside.
And who are you going to vote
out tonight and why?
>> I'm voting for Ashley
because I think she's the
weakest link in the group.
>> PROBST: Ashley, why would it
make sense from a tribe's point
of view to get rid of you?
>> Honestly, I don't think I'm
the weakest one and I'm not
bringing a negative energy
around the tribe either.
>> I don't approach people with
negativity.
I react.
If you come at me nice and
sweet, you're going to get nice
and sweet.
You come at me with some trash,
you're going to get some trash.
>> Here's the thing-- when
someone is in camp screaming
and yelling at other people
constantly about everything,
that puts everyone in a
bad mood.
>> Who have I screamed and
yelled at, Jaison?
>> You have yelled at Ashley.
You have yelled at Marisa.
You yelled at one of our guests
who came.
Anybody who asks you a question
or tries to do something on
their own, you constantly
correct them and tell them
they're doing it wrong.
>> Not true. That's not true.
>> That's absolutely true.
>> Is that true?
>> 100% true.
>> When you have asked me to do
things--
>> Amazing how you always try
to go to someone that you think
is weak.
That's what bullies do.
You yell at every single girl.
>> I'm not a bully.
You're a... baby, dude.
>> Don't ask her. Talk to me.
>> You have these temper
tantrums after every challenge,
like, "Oh, I don't want to be on
the team."
>> "Oh my God, I'm an outlaw.
I'm a renegade!
They splashed me in the face, I
can't tackle anyone now, sorry.
I got splashed."
>> Okay, Ivy League, keep it up.
>> Who are you trying to kid?
Who are you trying to fool?
>> I'm not trying to kid
anybody.
>> PROBST: Natalie, what's it
like being in the middle of
this?
>> Um, I was just kind of
leaning back just in case fists
go flying, 'cause I don't want
it to be me getting hit.
>> PROBST: Russell, you're a guy
that likes to get scrappy.
Explain to me what's going on
between Ben and Jaison.
>> I think that it's just Ben
said some negative things that
might have been, uh, racial.
>> They might have been racial?
Okay.
>> And it affected the way
Jaison thought about him, and
that was it.
That was the end of the
relationship.
>> PROBST: Jaison, you guys
still have a chance in
this game.
You're down four after tonight.
But you're not out.
Is there any way you could heal
this wound?
>> I just have to draw a line
in the sand, and I have to say
that, you know, there is no $1
million that is worth me
sitting up here with him
anymore.
I mean, I sat here and watched
him scream at Yasmin at our
camp, and over here, saying
incredible things.
So is there a way to patch this
rift?
I don't think so.
But I'm not going to sit in
camp and listen to this guy
anymore. I'm just not.
>> PROBST: Ben, big reaction
from him.
>> I have said from the get-go,
everybody knows I've been very,
very consistent.
I have not started one fight,
not started one.
>> That's not even what I was
talking about.
I was talking more about the
ghetto trash that you tried to
call her over there.
>> Okay, well, if she's from
the ghetto and she's trashy,
that's ghetto trash.
I'm sorry.
That's not racial whatsoever.
That's where you're from and
how you're acting.
That's ghetto trash.
>> If that's really what you
think, Ben.
>> So if you can't understand
that--
>> Let me make another point,
then Southern guy with
Southern ways.
Do you really think you should
talk to a woman that way?
>> You know what, if she is
going to be disrespectful--
Southern gentleman, do you
speak to a young lady that way?
>> She's not a lady.
>> Really, she wasn't a lady?
I mean, come on.
>> Ladies have manners, okay?
This girl right here, Southern,
has manners.
Says yes, sir, yes, ma'am,
please, thank you.
So, Yasmin is being a bitch,
then she's not a lady.
I mean, it's not that hard.
>> Okay.
>> There was nothing racial that
I said.
>> Okay, whatever.
>> It was strictly what I saw.
>> If you say so.
>> How she was acting
towards me.
So, if you want to call it a
racial game and play that card,
then go for it, buddy.
>> You know, you should have
some sensitivity to history,
and historically when certain
comments are made and directed
toward certain people, it is
because of race.
I mean, if what you're telling
me is that what you said had
absolutely no racial context,
then maybe Yasmin was right and
you are ignorant.
Maybe you really don't get it.
>> PROBST: Ashley, any time
there's heat on somebody else,
it means it's not on you.
Gotta make you feel great.
>> Well, I've known the last
couple of days that he's going
to vote for me, but there's
definitely other tension, so it
does leave it a little off me.
But I packed my bags.
I mean, you never know what
happens in the game.
>> PROBST: Ben, is there
anything you've said that you
regret and you would like to say
to Jaison now, "dude, I didn't
mean anything by it"?
>> Not anything I can think of.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: All right, it's time
to get to the vote, which
means, Shambo, it's time for
you to go.
You have certainly heard a lot
tonight.
What you share with your
tribe mates, up to you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
Good night.
All right, it is time to vote.
Mick, you're up.
>> I just really think you need
to grow up.
That's all I have to say to you.
>> You knew it was coming.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally
the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Ashley.
Ben.
One vote Ashley, one vote Ben.
Two votes Ben, one vote Ashley.
Ben.
That's three votes Ben, one
vote Ashley.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa-- Ben.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Thank God.
>> PROBST: Ben, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
I'm not sure I have much to
offer you guys.
You've got to figure out how to
turn things around.
Or I will be seeing you back
here at Tribal Council.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I'm tired.
I'm hungry.
>> PROBST: Russell gets fed up
with Jaison.
>> What kind of man is that?
>> PROBST: And at Galu...
>> Wherever the immunity idol
is on their beach is probably
on our beach.
>> PROBST: It's not so easy to
find a hidden immunity idol.
>> Well, I think it's pretty
funny that I'm going home
because I think everybody's
going to starve.
I think it's even funnier that
it's raining.
'Cause you guys are going to be
wet.
I'm really not worried about it.
I'm glad I'm getting a nice,
dry sleep tonight.
The tribe is a bunch of
sissies, everybody except
Russell.
I was the hardest working guy
in camp, everybody knew that.
They'll miss me when I'm gone.