>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> To our new tribe.
>> PROBST: After the two tribes
merged, the old Galu had a
comfortable eight-four advantage
over the old Foa Foa.
>> The plan for Foa Foa is to
shoot them down-- pop, pop,
pop, pop.
>> PROBST: But while the old
Galu was basking in the glow of
victory...
>> No.
>> PROBST: ...they were blind to
the fact that Shambo felt
ostracized by Laura and embraced
by Russell.
>> Shambo hates Laura, so I know
at any point, she'll vote
Laura's name.
>> PROBST: They also didn't
realize that Natalie was working
the Galu women to take out a
Galu man.
>> I don't trust Erik.
>> All of a sudden, all the
girls want to vote Erik out, but
they could possibly be saying,
"Let's say vote Erik," and then
they get me and the idol.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
both Russell and Erik showed up
with hidden immunity idols.
Erik's idol stayed in his
pocket because he was sure that
he wasn't in danger.
>> I would be floored if I saw
them get one Galu member to
turn.
>> PROBST: Russell was sure that
he was in danger, so he played
his idol.
Any votes cast for Russell
tonight will not count.
But he didn't need to because
Natalie's plan worked.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa and the first
member of our jury-- Erik.
Thanks to Natalie, the old Galu
blindsided one of their own.
The tribe has spoken.
Although the Foa Foa four have
lived to see another day, their
battle is far from over.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(crickets chirping)
>> I'd just like a chocolate
chip cookie...
>> Uh-huh.
>> ...with, like, one-inch thick
of peanut butter on it.
>> Ooh.
>> Thanks, Shambo.
>> At Tribal today, I had a
strong feeling it would be me.
Uh, I didn't even think twice
about playing the idol.
But I'm really worried, because
I'm pretty sure I'm out next.
I'm gone.
>> So, I'm hoping for a miracle,
because I'm in deep trouble
right now.
>> That was perfect.
>> Yeah.
>> That could not have been
better, girls.
>> Well, because...
>> Well, no, because...
>> I wanted...
We needed to make him nervous.
I think it was the dumbest move
that Russell could have made,
playing that idol tonight.
When he stood up and he used it,
I about came off my stool.
It could not have happened any
better for us, because not only
did we get rid of Erik, we just
flushed out that idol and then
exposed who's going to be
coming up next.
It could not have happened any
better.
Russell should absolutely be
nervous.
Russell is going to be gone
next.
♪ ♪
(squeaking)
>> I have no idea how to do
this.
Well, I kind of went out for a
walk, and I stumble upon this
rat or this mouse.
I'm so scared.
Oh, my gosh!
A rock or a stick?
I really ca...
Oh, my gosh!
I'm, like, oh, my goodness,
that's, like, something to eat.
I was just thinking, I'm
starving.
I never thought I'd be this
hungry in my life.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, just turn around, eat
your... eat your snack.
Eat your snack.
Eat your snack, buddy.
Oh, gosh. Oh, my word.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, this is pitiful.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, Lord, have mercy.
Oh, my word.
Okay.
Finally, I just hit the rat.
It was really hard for me 'cause
he was looking at me.
He was cute, but I knew how...
I'm starving.
I've never been this hungry in
my entire life.
I feel like I'm just fading
away.
Um, I have something to show
y'all.
>> What do you got?
>> Yeah?
>> I killed something, y'all.
>> What'd you kill?
>> A rat.
>> What...?
>> I swear, y'all, I swear.
It's right here.
>> What? Ew!
>> I know, it's disgusting.
Would you have done it?
>> How did you kill a rat?
>> With a stick.
It was scary.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Russell!
>> What?
>> Natalie walks into camp with
this rat in a coconut, and we're
all just shocked.
>> Did you catch that?
>> Get it? Got it?
>> Well, I killed it.
I hit it with a stick and then
the rock. I just don't know...
>> Are you serious?
>> Yeah.
>> She came into this game the
Southern belle, you know, very
sweet, nice girl, but definitely
not the rough-and-tumble
Survivor type.
She wasn't a Shambo.
So when she came back in her
little bikini with a rat in the
coconut, we were all shocked to
death.
>> Beef jerky.
>> Oh, that's so good.
>> It kind of just tastes like
chicken.
>> On so many levels, I'm proud
of Natalie out here.
You know, from what I knew about
her coming in to where she is
now, I think she's changed a lot
over the last 23 days, and I'm
really happy for her.
>> You're a rock star hunter and
gatherer.
>> Oh, thanks!
>> You believe, girl.
>> Oh, we got a little tree
mail.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Isn't that nice?
>> What else is in here?
Nothing.
(laughter)
>> I found the other idol,
everybody.
>> Yeah.
If there's another immunity idol
that gets put into play, I'm
going to find it, because I'm
probably gone next time.
So I have to believe there's
one here.
>> Tree mail!
>> "And now for something
completely different.
A challenge with a digital
display!
You'll work together with a
bunch of nuts, to win a feast
and a getaway!"
>> Oh!
>> The second immunity idol-- I
think it's in the camp right
now, and I think I'm going to
find it today.
But we've got a reward challenge
coming up, so right now, I don't
have time, but I'm working on
it.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will divide into
two teams of five.
On my go, you will race two at
a time out into a field to
collect a series of poles
threaded with white and black
coconuts.
Once you've retrieved the poles,
arrange them so that the white
coconuts form a four-digit
number.
Each team's number is different,
so you're not going to be able
to cheat.
Once you have the number, I'll
blindfold a tribe member.
Using only their sense of touch,
they must find the same number
on a combination lock.
The first team to solve their
combination lock and raise their
flag wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing
for?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: The winning team will
be taken directly from here to
a one-of-a-kind massive rock
slide.
This is a natural rock slide
that you literally slide down
the rocks into beautiful fresh
water.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: You'll also enjoy a
nice picnic lunch.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Fried chicken.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Chocolate brownies.
>> Oh...
>> Oh, no!
>> Chocolate.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Okay, we're going to
have a random draw for our
teams, and because there are 11
of you, that means one person
will not participate in this
challenge.
All right, we've chosen our
teams.
Jaison, Laura, Brett, Mick and
Russell-- that's our yellow
team.
Shambo, Kelly, Dave, John and
Monica are the purple team.
That leaves you, Natalie, as
the odd one out.
Here's the twist for you.
You will not participate in the
challenge.
What you're going to do instead
is choose one team to support.
If you choose the team that goes
on to win, you go on reward with
them.
If you choose the team that ends
up losing, you go back with them
to camp empty-handed.
Big decision.
Look at the two teams.
Who do you think has the best
shot of winning?
>> They look like a pretty
good... a pretty good match.
I guess I will go with Brett,
Laura, Mick, Russ and Jaison.
>> PROBST: Natalie, going to
support the yellow team.
Natalie, you'll take a spot on
the bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize, we'll get
started.
All right, you're going out two
at a time.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Mick and Brett, John and Kelly.
>> Come on, guys!
>> Let's go, guys!
>> PROBST: Got to get those knot
untied!
>> Got it. Got it.
>> PROBST: Kelly and John
heading back with the first pole
for purple.
Mick and Brett heading back with
the first pole for yellow.
Go!
>> Hey, guys.
>> PROBST: Dave and Shambo
heading out for purple.
Russell and Jaison now heading
out for yellow.
>> Let's go, Jaison and Russell!
>> Got it?
>> I-I got it.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Jaison and Russell
quickly heading back.
Dave and Shambo heading back.
Go, yellow!
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> PROBST: Brett and Mick out on
the course for yellow.
Yellow's now in the lead.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Kelly and John back
out on the course for purple.
Mick and Brett rip through
those knots.
John and Kelly making fast work
of it, trying to make up some
time.
>> Move! Move! Move! Move!
>> Come on, guys!
Come on!
>> PROBST: John and Kelly
closing the gap.
We are neck and neck!
>> Yeah, come on.
>> PROBST: Russell and Jaison
back out on the course.
They are going for their last
pole.
Dave and Shambo.
Shambo really slowing purple
down.
>> Come on, Sham!
Come on, Sham!
>> PROBST: That gives yellow a
lot of advantage.
>> Let's go Jaison, Russell!
You guys got it.
>> PROBST: Jaison and Russell
heading back with that final
pole.
>> Go, go, go!
>> Let's go guys!
>> PROBST: They've all made
quick work of the knots for
purple.
Yellow still in the lead.
>> Got it! Got it! Push it!
>> Run, Shambo, run!
>> PROBST: Dave and Shambo
heading back with that final
pole for purple.
Start working on it, yellow.
>> Good job, guys.
Let's go yellow.
Study it good.
>> Let's go! Let's go!
>> PROBST: Go, purple.
>> Put them up, put them up.
Dave and Shambo, put them up.
>> PROBST: You are now looking
to form a four-digit number
using the white coconuts.
>> Put this one at the very top.
>> Oh, my God.
>> We both take this one, we
have a three.
>> Just grab it.
>> Good job, guys, come on,
guys.
Hustle, stick with it, you can
do it.
>> Three.
>> Put this one in the middle.
>> Come on, champ.
>> Six.
>> One.
>> That's not a three, that's
not a three.
>> This is a four.
>> It could be a three.
>> This one-- the top one needs
to rotate.
Watch out, guys.
>> That makes it a four.
All right.
Drop this, Shambo.
Shambo, grab this.
>> PROBST: Dave has an idea.
Barking out orders now.
>> Good girl, good girl.
That's the girl.
>> What if we rotate this middle
one, that turns this into a six?
Let's rotate this one.
>> Rotate this one?
>> Okay, this one.
>> Come on, hustle, hustle,
hustle.
>> That's a three, that's a
seven.
No.
We need a six.
We got it, we got it.
Four, six, seven, three.
Monica!
>> Yes!
>> Four, six, seven, three.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Purple has their
number, they've passed it on to
Monica.
Each team's number is different.
That means yellow can't cheat
off purple.
Yellow still looking for those
four digits.
>> You got tons of time, Monica,
relax.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Monica now working on
the puzzle for purple.
She must now find the same four
numbers her teammates found
below while blindfolded, using
only her fingers.
>> Please, dear God.
>> There's a three, there's a
four, there's a six.
There's a seven.
Seven, three, four, six.
>> Okay, got it.
Come on.
>> Hurry, hurry, tell him.
>> Seven, three, four, six.
>> PROBST: Laura now working on
the puzzle for yellow.
>> Come on, Moni.
>> PROBST: Monica had a nice
head start.
Can she keep the lead?
>> Keep going, Monica.
>> PROBST: Laura not panicking.
>> Keep working, keep working.
>> Laura, seven, three, four,
six.
>> PROBST: Now it's a matter of
who is going to finish first.
>> No, no, no.
>> PROBST: Monica thinks she has
it.
>> Four, six, seven, three,
Moni.
>> PROBST: It is wrong.
Keep working.
>> Keep going.
>> They're not done.
>> Seven, three, four, six.
>> PROBST: Monica has it right.
Purple wins reward!
(cheers and applause)
>> Right on.
Good job, Moni.
>> You rock, little sister.
>> Thank you.
>> Good job.
Nice.
>> That's a girl.
Good girl.
>> PROBST: Natalie, you can join
yellow.
Natalie, Russell, Mick, Brett,
Jaison, Laura, got nothing for
you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Enjoy.
>> Thanks, man, good job.
You guys were tough.
>> PROBST: Dave, Shambo, Kelly,
John, Monica, congratulations.
You will leave from here and be
taken to a beautiful spot.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Have a good afternoon.
♪ ♪
(John laughs)
>> Today's reward is awesome.
The rock slides are killer.
>> Careful.
How high is that?
(Monica screaming)
(laughter)
>> Whoa.
>> The slides are big and fast
and fun.
The pools are cool.
It's kind of what I've been
looking forward to for a while--
just a day of relaxation.
>> I'm, like, so terrified of
water slides.
(Kelly screaming)
It was so fun just, like, going
down.
It's fresh water and it's clean,
it's clear, and...
(Kelly and Monica screaming)
...it's just been beautiful
here.
>> Mmm.
Cheers.
>> Cheers.
>> My family's from Puerto Rico,
and it totally reminds me of
Puerto Rico and waterfalls and
the rain forest.
It reminds me of my family and a
lot of the vacations we used to
take as kids.
These doughnuts are, like,
redonkulous.
The food is fantastic, and
having these waterfalls surround
you altogether makes for an
amazing reward.
Cheers.
>> Sweet tea.
>> And lemon, too.
>> Okay.
"So you've won a reward,
You'll have fun and you'll eat.
But you didn't come here for
food,
You came here to compete.
Clue #1
The real prize is information,
On how to stay safe in this
game.
Hidden at your camp is an idol,
And 'Immunity' is its name."
>> I say we share the info with
all the Galus and we got a, we
got a free trigger to pull.
>> There is another hidden
immunity idol that has been put
into play that is hiding at camp
somewhere.
So because there's no members of
the old Foa Foa here, we're
going to keep that information
strictly, you know, Galu right
now.
>> I'm happy just with everyone
here.
(Dave burps)
>> Right now I'm starting to
feel more and more comfortable
with the plan of sort of
knocking off Foa Foa after Foa
Foa.
>> We need to get a Foa Foa gone
for sure.
Who-- do you think Russell?
>> Hmm?
>> Who do you think should go
from Foa Foa?
>> I don't want Russell to go.
>> I know, but he's super
strategic.
>> He's strategic, but he sucks
at challenges.
We can beat him.
>> Shambo-- she's protecting
Russell, you know?
Russell's one of the most
conniving players I feel like we
have going in the game right
now.
Like, he needs to go.
Yeah.
>> Because Russell didn't even
have a clue.
>> I know.
>> If I had to pick one person
that would, I think, go over to
Foa Foa, it would definitely be
Shambo.
But whether Shambo's with us or
not, we still have six to five
if she goes with them, and we
don't really need them.
>> I don't care about no damn
reward.
I'm here to win the game.
I'm gonna find the next immunity
idol and I ain't going to tell a
damn soul.
You know, I thought maybe it
might be around tree mail, it
might be around the water, or it
might be around the bridge.
It has to be near something-- a
landmark, something.
It cannot be any other place.
That's where it has to be,
around them areas.
That easy.
Think I just found the second
hidden immunity idol without a
clue.
(laughs)
This is crazy.
This might be worth one million
dollars.
This is it-- number two.
This is amazing.
Am I that damn good?
(laughs)
This is just unprecedented.
I missed fried chicken and
brownies for the second hidden
immunity idol.
Sounds like a good exchange to
me.
>> All right, dude.
All righty, then.
>> Yesterday, I found the
immunity idol without anybody
telling me anything.
Well, I think I want to share
something with you.
Not two in a row, that's just
the gift that I have.
This was why I was born.
I was going to keep it to
myself, but we only have four
people left from Foa Foa.
So you have to have help with
it.
I can trust you more than I can
trust anybody out here.
>> As I do you.
>> So...
>> Dude, you do...
you are...
Tell me you...
>> So you're going to have
to... you're going to have to
to help me help you.
>> Dude, dude, her head is
getting fricking lopped off.
>> You're right.
We vote Laura.
>> It's a samurai sword.
>> This is just going to be a
wonderful thing.
Shocker.
>> You lucky bastard!
I cannot believe you found both
those fricking immunity idols.
>> The lucky thing helps
us both.
>> Oh, my God!
I have been pretty much aligned
with Foa Foa for the last
two weeks.
I really hit it off with those
guys, created some really great
relationships.
Russ is probably the one guy in
this game that I impeccably
trust.
>> You're right in the same boat
I'm in right now.
>> That is so funny.
>> Right now it has no holes.
It had holes and it was a
sinking ship before, but we
patched them up.
>> Wow!
>> It's time to sail on.
(laughter)
You know, I'm going to need help
to make sure my name is on the
chopping block.
>> That's already been put into
motion.
This is going to be
unbelievable.
Our plan is let them vote
Russell, so when six of them
vote Russell, we'll come back
and vote Laura.
He'll play the hidden immunity
idol and she'll go home.
So I am so excited.
The only thing that can derail
this is her winning immunity.
>> If Medusa wins immunity, we
get rid of one of her posse.
Yup.
And then she's going to be
scrambling.
>> They have a disdain for
Monica-- the boys do-- that
will eliminate her immediately.
But nobody's got anything on
Kelly, nobody's got anything
against Kelly, so Kelly's a
bigger threat than Monica.
>> Right.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys.
Guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first,
I'll take back the immunity
necklaces.
>> You can borrow it for a
little while, Jeff.
>> PROBST: I'm going to be
giving it back to you?
All right, I like it.
Thank you, Laura.
Today, only one immunity
necklace.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
use a grappling hook to retrieve
two bags, each containing a
puzzle peg.
The first three to get their
bags move on to the final round
where you must place one of
those pegs in its appropriate
spot on the board.
Each time you place a peg,
another one drops down.
First person to get all their
pegs in the right spot wins
immunity.
Guaranteed a one in ten shot at
a million dollars.
All right, we'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
First three to get both their
bags move on to the final round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Bit of a learning curve.
How much rope to hold onto.
Nice toss by Russell.
Just misses the bag, but a great
toss.
Shambo makes a snag.
Now she's got to reel it in.
Shambo has her first bag.
Mick with a good toss.
He hooks it.
Mick got his first bag.
Kelly has her first bag.
Brett on target.
Brett has his first bag.
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Mick has his second
bag.
Making quick work of it.
Mick moving on.
Looking for two more people.
Natalie with her first bag, but
she loses it.
>> My hook's stuck.
>> PROBST: Go get it.
Jaison with his first bag.
Laura with the long toss.
Laura has her first bag.
Russell just barely hooks a bag.
Got his first one.
Shambo with a good toss.
And she hooks it!
>> Got it, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Shambo has both bags.
Shambo's moving on!
One more person moving on.
Laura, Kelly, Brett, Jaison,
Russell, all looking for that
last bag.
Russell with a good toss.
Can he turn it into a snag?
He does.
Russell has his second bag!
Laura has her second bag!
It's a race!
Russell loses his!
Laura has hers!
Laura moving on!
Laura, Mick, Shambo moving on
to the final round.
Here we go.
Final round for immunity is
Laura, Mick, and Shambo.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Each bag has a peg.
One peg will fit in that board,
one peg will not fit.
You have to choose the right
one to start your sequence.
Mick has both his pegs.
Trying to find a spot.
The question is, which is the
first peg to fit?
Shambo has both her pegs.
Once you find that first one,
it will start the sequence.
Shambo has her first piece.
Shambo places another piece.
>> Yeah, Sham.
>> PROBST: Mick trying to
force it.
Is it right?
Mick has his first piece.
>> Go, Mick.
>> PROBST: Laura has both
her pegs.
Shambo with another piece.
>> Come on, Sham.
>> Relax, relax.
Think, think.
>> PROBST: Mick has another
piece.
Immunity on the line.
A guaranteed one-in-ten shot at
a million bucks.
Laura has her first piece.
Laura has her second piece.
Shambo places another one.
Laura with her third piece now.
Laura places another piece.
Laura like clockwork on this,
like she's done this before.
Laura with another one!
>> All you got to do is look at,
look at the piece.
>> PROBST: Mick studying while
Laura continues to place
pieces effortlessly.
>> Total square, total square,
total square.
>> PROBST: Laura really running
away with the challenge
right now.
Gonna have to work to catch
catch Laura.
>> Look at the piece.
Look at the piece.
>> Come on.
>> Arrow left, arrow left,
arrow left.
>> PROBST: Laura still talking
to herself, and it's working.
>> Right there.
Laura getting very close.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Laura down to her
last piece.
Laura wins individual immunity!
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
>> Good job, girl.
>> PROBST: Laura, come on over.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Back-to-back
immunity wins.
Laura is safe at tonight's
Tribal Council.
As for the rest of you, one of
you going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Congratulations.
>> Thanks.
>> Right now, we're just
getting rid of Foa Foa.
Clearly, Russell's the first one
to go because he's lied to
us all.
I see the Galu tribe voting for
Russell, including Natalie.
I think she wants to make good
that she's in, so tonight
Russell's going home.
>> Good job, Laura.
>> Oh, the challenge sucked
'cause Laura won, and now we
can't vote her off, and my heart
is broken.
I'm so sad.
I'm pissed.
I think you always have to have
a plan B, and I said in the
off chance that she did get
immunity today, that we'd vote
Kel 'cause Kelly's stronger
than Monica.
Monica's no threat whatsoever.
So eliminate somebody that's
close to Laura, cause a little
dissension amongst the ranks.
That's the plan of attack.
>> I found another
immunity idol.
>> Bull ...
Where'd you find it?
>> At the bridge.
>> Nicely done, my man.
You deserve this, man.
You deserve this, for real.
>> Dude...
>> Listen...
>> I know what's happening.
Hopefully, they trying to vote
me out.
So trust me, just vote Kelly.
Everything else is fine.
>> So Russell found another
idol that the Galu members don't
know about.
And, uh, the idea is to
surprise them with it.
It's a gamble, baby.
>> It's a gamble.
>> All right, I'm with you.
If Galu gets wind of what's
going on, they're gonna change
their vote and they'll take
somebody on Foa Foa out that's
not Russell, and it's all a
waste.
So it's gotta to be Russell
tonight or we're all through.
>> There's an immunity idol.
So the idea is to focus all
the attention on Russell...
>> He found another one?
>> He found another.
It's under the bridge.
Hi. What's going on?
>> So Russell found the idol.
It's unbelievable how he finds
these things.
And so quickly, too.
He just has a keen mind for it,
you know?
>> I'm really beginning to love
that guy.
I'm really beginning
to love him.
>> He's good at this thing.
I didn't know there would be a
second one.
So I'm excited to see what
happens tonight at
Tribal Council.
We all hope to put a dent in
Galu today and put a big dent in
that arrogance and
condescending patronizing
attitude they have towards us.
>> So remind me-- Russell,
Natalie, Mick, Jaison, right?
>> Should we plan for just in
case that one of them may find
an idol?
Because if we all vote for
Russell, and then say Russell
has the idol again, at that
point the other person goes
home, and it's one of us.
>> That... All right, listen.
We can't worry about that
right now.
Now's not the time for that.
Like, they don't know anything
about it.
>> I can tell you if it were me
and I was on Foa Foa and I were
over here...
>> I'd be looking for the idol.
>> I would assume that
it was here.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I mean, that's not rocket
science.
>> Which means they found it
just by digging in tree stumps,
though.
>> He found a fricking idol
without a fricking clue.
>> Here's, here's the thing
that...
Here's what I, here's all...
No, no, no, no.
That's what makes me nervous,
right?
>> I don't think he has it.
I don't think he even...
If he suspects there's one
here, I'd be surprised.
First vote-- Russ, second vote
Natalie, bang...
or vice versa.
We can go Natalie first, we can
go Russ second.
>> I say Russ first.
I say Russ.
>> I don't know.
>> I think I heard that they
were gonna vote Natalie.
I don't know that, but I heard
them say her name.
That's how this game goes.
It messes with your mind.
I think they made their mind
up; I think it might be Natalie.
>> You think it's Natalie?
Why do you think that?
>> I don't know. (laughs)
>> You got few hours
to try and sway it to make sure.
>> I don't know if I should
play it or not.
I'm confused on what to do.
I don't want to be the dumbass
that gets voted out with the
idol in his pocket, and I don't
want to be the dumbass that
uses the idol again, and then
nobody votes my name.
So now, I don't know what to do
with it.
>> And as soon as we burn all
the Foa Foas, kill a chicken.
>> Yeah!
>> It's our Galu chicken,
it's not theirs.
>> Yeah, it's not theirs.
>> We're making it pure Galu
all the way.
>> I'm not sharing with anybody
that ain't purple.
>> That's right.
Right now, I think we're tight.
The Galu tribe is tight.
We don't trust Sham, but we are
still definitely six strong.
As long as we can get the Foa
Foa out, and then we have seven
of the Galu left, that's what
we want.
>> I like that.
I'm there.
>> PROBST: I'll now bring in
the first member of our jury.
Erik voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
So, Dave, coming into last
Tribal, Galu had the numbers,
eight to four.
You voted out one of your own
in Erik.
Is that a sign that old tribal
lines are gone and this now is
an individual game?
>> Not at all, Jeff.
To be honest, our tribe was
weakened from within by Erik's
presence.
And it was actually a
strengthening of our tribal
unity.
>> PROBST: Kelly, how did you
feel about last tribal's vote?
>> I think there was this
uneasiness in the tribe, almost
like a snake kind of starting a
lot of trouble and it seemed to
all come back to Erik.
So when it comes down to it,
you have to go with who you
trust.
>> PROBST: Natalie, what's it
like at camp?
The old Galu tribe is still in
charge, in terms of numbers,
and it's their camp.
>> I think they're trying to
make us still feel welcome,
like we're all one.
>> PROBST: How could they
possibly make you feel like
you're all still one?
>> You know, I've been welcomed
into the shelter, I sleep with
them.
>> PROBST: But Natalie, you're
not all still one.
>> You're right.
But they're not, like, being
mean or ugly to anybody.
I guess that's more or less
what I was trying to say.
But the fact of the matter is,
it is seven to four and they are
tight.
>> PROBST: Jaison, what does it
say to the Foa Foa foursome
that Galu was willing to get
rid of one of their own?
>> They're very tight-lipped
about what's going on over
there, so it's hard to figure
out if there is a crack or not.
You never know what can happen.
Maybe there's another Erik out
there that hasn't been exposed
yet.
So I'm just trying to hold on
to some hope.
>> PROBST: Shambo, tell me the
state of the game right now,
from where you sit.
>> It feels like the original
Galu is pretty comfortable, and
the Foa Foa is kind of holding
on.
>> PROBST: So, Mick, if old
tribal lines are holding
strong, your only chance is to
keep chipping away.
Otherwise, your days are
numbered.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
I mean, we know that, the
numbers are obvious.
But we still hope somebody will
see past the former Galu,
former Foa Foa, and just see
four solid votes and be like "I
need to make a big move here."
>> PROBST: Russell, so do you
spend most of your day
observing the Galu seven,
trying to figure out-- maybe
there's a crack here, maybe I
can get in over here?
>> Well, yeah, I did.
But now, you know, it's getting
to where we're hoping that
somebody comes to us.
Talks to us and wants to do
something.
But they seem to be pretty
tight.
>> PROBST: Monica, do you see
Foa Foa people going up to your
tribe mates, trying to see if
they can start some drama?
>> I think the Foa Foa see how
strong the seven of us are, at
this point.
If they are giving it a try, I
give them respect for doing so,
but I don't think it's that
hard of a try that they're
giving.
>> PROBST: So at this point in
the game, Dave, how do you
decide who's next?
>> I think you just have to
assess who's the most
dangerous, and there are
several different criteria, not
the least of which is physical
ability, mental toughness,
strategic acumen.
And it's a communal decision,
you know?
We try to come to a consensus
so that everybody feels heard
and everybody feels that their
needs are being met.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Laura, once again, you have the
immunity necklace, keeping it
for yourself?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: You can not vote for
Laura.
Anybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Brett, you're up.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has a hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
>> I ain't finished playing
just yet.
Keep hope alive.
>> PROBST: The rules of
Survivor state that if
someone plays a hidden immunity
idol, then any votes cast
against that person will not
count and the person with the
next-highest number of votes
will be sent home.
This is an idol.
Any votes cast against Russell
will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote--
Russell.
Does not count.
That's three votes Russell,
none of them count.
Russell.
Does not count.
We still have no votes for
anybody.
Russell.
Does not count.
Kelly.
>> You're kidding me.
>> PROBST: That's one vote
Kelly.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Two votes Kelly.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa and the second
member of our jury, Kelly.
That's three.
Tonight, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Wow.
PROBST: Kelly, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, since the merge, there
have been two Tribal Councils,
two blind sides, two hidden
immunity idols played and, once
again, the Foa Foa foursome
have survived the vote.
The question is, will tonight's
vote change the game or merely
delay the inevitable?
One more thing: the hidden
immunity idol goes back into
the game once again.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor, it's a showdown
between Russell and Laura.
>> It's only a matter of time,
Russ.
>> I'm ten times smatter than
she could ever be.
>> PROBST: And finding the next
idol means everything.
>> They're moving.
>> Go get them.
Let's follow them.
>> Come on, Dave.
>> We need to keep that hidden
immunity idol out of Russell's
hands.
>> I definitely, definitely
wasn't expecting to be going
home tonight.
Everything was working out
perfectly and I hope Galu gets
rid of Russell.
It's too many idols.
How many can there be.
He's just a little sneaky man
and I definitely know that he's
next on the line.
Foa Foa stepped in and totally
I think took us all by surprise.
I don't know if anyone from my
tribe was involved but I'm
totally shocked.