>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
>> I'm in control of this game.
Everything has worked for me so
far.
I set up my alliance so strong.
My people-- they come up to me,
they tell me everything.
>> PROBST: By day 30, Russell
was driving on cruise control,
mowing down anyone who got in
his way.
>> Now I can comfortably sit on
my throne and watch everybody
bicker at each other.
>> PROBST: He felt so
comfortable that he let his
guard down and revealed a
secret.
Meanwhile, Shambo had what she
thought was a psychic vision.
>> I had a dream last night we
voted Dave off.
>> PROBST: So she immediately
decided that's what everyone had
to do.
>> I am definitely in a position
of power.
Dave is so gone.
>> PROBST: But Russell decided
that John was the one who needed
to go, so he told everyone but
Shambo to switch their votes.
>> The best way to do this...
>> Uh-huh.
>> ...is John.
It will be you if it's not John.
>> PROBST: Jaison was worried
about going against Shambo's
wishes because her vote is
critical to keeping a majority.
>> You piss off Shambo and she's
going to go to the other side.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, Jaison and everyone but
Shambo followed Russell's lead.
Tenth person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury--
John.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Wow.
John was majorly blindsided, as
was I.
I had no idea they were voting
John.
The plan was to vote Dave, and I
am positively stunned.
Okay.
>> So he was trying to get rid
of you, and I didn't want you
to, to, uh...
>> Break my word.
>> Break your word to him.
>> I couldn't have.
I would have written Dave down
anyway.
>> So everything's still cool.
I don't want you to worry.
Nothing's going crazy or
nothing.
>> All right.
>> My damage control with Shambo
definitely worked.
I just lied to her, which is
exactly what I've been doing
this whole time.
I've lied about almost every
aspect of my life.
I'm the richest man here, but I
lied about what I do for a
living because I'll do whatever
it takes to win this game.
>> All right, good night.
This is too easy.
♪ ♪
>> Oh, no.
We're just kind of shooting the
breeze, letting...
>> Oh.
The game's not over yet, you
know.
>> Oh, no, no, not at all.
>> Of all the people still here,
who would you guys vote for, I
mean, if you were on the jury?
>> Russell and Mick could get a
lot of votes.
>> Yeah, I think they could.
I think they will.
>> I think Russell is the
biggest threat by far.
>> Yeah.
>> 'Cause people are gonna be
like, "That guy played an insane
game."
>> Right.
>> It's always interesting to me
because behind the scenes, it
really has been me and Russell
making decisions, but...
>> Right, right.
>> I kind of left him out there
to be the aggressive bulldog
while I kind of stayed behind
the scenes, trying to be nice.
>> Oh, no, that could ruin you.
>> Apparently, that was a...
No, honestly, and I'm beginning
to think that was the wrong
strategy.
This is an interesting phase in
the game because you really have
to start thinking about winning
over the jury, and the way that
I'm gonna try to play the jury
is that the decisions that we
made were group decisions.
I had a big part in those
decisions.
It wasn't just Russell
unilaterally doing this.
Plus, you know, he was an
abrasive guy.
I was the more calm, cool, bond-
with-you kind of guy, so I feel
like I'm the guy that should get
that million dollars.
>> I mean, if I was in your
situation...
>> The interesting thing about
day 36 is that at that point,
there's no hidden immunity idols
anymore.
There's no nothing, so it's--
everyone gets an equal vote,
and...
>> Just make it to day 36.
>> Yeah.
>> Today I found out that
Russell already has a lot of
money, and I'm starting to see
some of the cracks in their
armor, and I think this will be
the time that tests their
loyalty to each other,
especially as they all have
different opinions of who they
see in the final three, so it's
just a matter of time before
that bomb ticks and then blows
up.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
>> Cool.
>> PROBST: All right, today, no
reward challenge.
Today we're playing for
immunity.
>> Everybody was expecting the
reward challenge.
I'm happier than the reward
'cause I'm ready to start
eliminating some people out
here.
I want to go to Tribal time and
time again.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to it?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Jaison, I will take back the
immunity necklace.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
take part in a Survivor bowling
tournament.
Here's how it works-- you will
be randomly matched up against
another person.
Your goal, very simple: roll the
ball down the lane, knock over
as many pins as you can.
You get two shots.
Winner moves on to the next
round.
Loser is out.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, guaranteed a one in
seven shot at a million bucks.
Guys ready to get to it?
>> Yes.
>> Make it happen.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for
matchups and we'll get started.
All right, Natalie and Shambo.
First matchup.
Choose a ball and roll.
Purple always goes first.
That's you, Natalie.
>> Oh, dear.
>> PROBST: Got to get the
jitters out.
Natalie throws a gutter ball on
her first roll, opening the door
for Shambo.
>> This is for all my friends
that play in a bowling league.
>> PROBST: Look at that.
>> Oh, Sham.
>> PROBST: Wow.
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Shambo with a nice
first ball of nine.
>> That was good.
(Dave whistles)
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Natalie, you have to
knock down at least nine pins or
you're out of this tournament
just like that.
>> Yeah, looks good.
>> PROBST: That's a good roll.
>> Wow, oh, wow.
>> PROBST: But not enough.
Natalie is out.
Shambo moves on to the next
round.
Next matchup-- Brett taking on
Russell.
Brett, gutter ball.
>> A little off.
That's all right.
>> Nicely done, Russell.
>> PROBST: Russell right down
the middle.
>> Oh, good job, Russ.
>> PROBST: Russell knocked down
four pins.
Brett, got to knock down at
least four or you are out.
That's not going to do it.
Brett is out of this challenge.
Russell moves on.
>> Good job, Russ.
>> PROBST: Next round-- Jaison
taking on Monica.
(Jaison groans)
>> PROBST: Jaison with two.
Nope.
Gutter ball for Monica.
>> Uh-oh, uh-oh.
>> PROBST: Total down-- six
pins.
Got your work cut out for you,
Monica.
That's down the middle.
You need six or more to stay
alive.
One won't do it.
Monica is out.
>> PROBST: Jaison moves on to
the next round.
Last round-- Mick taking on
Dave.
>> Let's go, Mick.
>> PROBST: Mick with a nice
first roll.
Mick knocks down four pins.
Dave Ball is up.
That's a nice shot right there.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: That's a strike!
First strike of the Survivor
tournament goes to Dave Ball.
Mick, knock down every pin to
force a tiebreaker.
You can do it.
Nope.
Falls short.
Mick is out.
Dave Ball moves on to the next
round.
Moving on to round two.
Draw for new matchups.
Shambo taking on Russ.
Jaison taking on Dave.
The winner of this matchup moves
on to the final round and will
have a shot at immunity.
>> Let's go, Sham.
>> PROBST: Nice roll by Shambo.
Shambo knocks down five pins
with her first roll.
>> Uh-oh.
>> PROBST: Russell knocks down
four pins.
>> Good job, Russ.
>> Oh, way off.
>> PROBST: Nothing for Shambo.
Russell, two gets you a win and
moves you on to the final round.
>> Go, Russ.
>> Oh.
>> Oh, wow.
>> PROBST: Russell doesn't pick
up any pins.
Russell is out.
Shambo is moving on to the final
round and a shot at immunity.
>> Good job, Sham.
>> Nice job, Sham.
>> PROBST: Next two-- Jaison
taking on Dave.
>> No.
>> PROBST: Nothing for Jaison.
Gutter ball for Dave Ball.
Jaison rolls his second ball and
it's a nice one.
>> Good job, Jaison.
>> PROBST: Jaison knocks over
seven pins.
>> Good job, Jaison.
>> PROBST: Dave needs seven pins
to stay in this, eight to win
it.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: That's not going to
do it.
Dave Ball is out.
Jaison moves on to the final
round against Shambo.
All right, it is Shambo taking
on Jaison.
Winner wins immunity.
Shambo with her first roll.
She gets nothing.
>> Go, Jaison, right down the
middle.
>> PROBST: Jaison with his first
roll.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Jaison gets nothing.
Pressure mounting.
Each player has one roll left.
>> Let's go, Sham.
>> Baby, right here, right now.
Come on.
>> PROBST: Shambo once again
comes up empty-handed.
>> Unbelievable.
>> PROBST: Jaison, all you have
to do is knock down one pin.
One pin...
>> That's all.
>> PROBST: ...and you have
immunity again.
>> Don't overthink it, man,
don't think.
>> PROBST: That's all you got
to do.
>> Go!
>> PROBST: Is it gonna hang on?
(others shout)
That will do it.
Jaison wins individual immunity
for the second time in a row!
>> Good job, Jaison!
>> Good job, Jai!
>> Good job, man!
>> PROBST: Jaison, come on over.
Nice job.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Once again, Jaison
is safe at tonight's Tribal
Council.
After 31 days, one of you going
home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I'll see you at Tribal.
Congrats.
>> Thanks.
>> When Dave did not win that
challenge, I was, like...
(whispers): "Buh-bye."
Dave's going home tonight.
♪ ♪
>> I'm gonna walk down the
beach, I think.
For me, the tide has turned.
I am low man on the pole.
All I know is somebody's going
home, and it ain't gonna be
Jaison.
>> Hey.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
I think the case for getting
rid of Dave primarily is because
that's who Shambo wants gone
right now.
And let's just keep the waters
calm, you know?
We stirred up enough by getting
rid of John-- we don't want
to... anger her, or get her
upset.
>> Well, what names are in your
head right now?
>> Right now, Dave's going home.
>> You think so?
>> I know so.
>> And that's just decided?
>> That's just it.
>> I just don't think that Dave
is this big threat that people
think he is, I really don't.
Right now I'm trying to stay a
little bit more passive and
really get into people's heads.
Russell is no fool.
He's not about to take someone
like Shambo that far who could
potentially get a lot of jury
votes.
I think we're underestimating
Shambo, though.
Shambo is a hard worker around
camp.
>> I know she is.
>> And let's face it, a majority
of the jury is Galu.
They look at Shambo as a strong
woman who really competed in
challenges and kept things
going around camp, who's
always in the running for
immunity.
>> Yeah, I see your point.
>> I just started to plant the
seed and make arguments that
would make Russell sweat.
I mean, with me on Dave's side
and whispering Shambo's name in
Russell's ear, anything can
happen.
I think you should still keep
options open.
>> Yeah.
I'm hearing you, that's for
sure.
I have a lot of options in the
game right now.
I can play different ways and
still be okay.
One option I have is keeping
Dave, because I know I can beat
Dave for the million dollars.
Just think, me, Dave, for a
million dollars?
It's a no-brainer.
I have to win.
So it's a good strategic move
to keep Dave around.
I'm gonna tell you, Dave.
>> All right, what's up, buddy?
>> Your best strategic move...
>> Uh-huh.
>> ...would be talking to me.
>> Mm.
>> I don't know why you ain't
came to me yet.
>> All right, well, it sounds
like you got some thoughts in
your mind.
>> Yes, I do.
>> I'd be interested in hearing
them.
>> Right now, everybody is
debating you and Shambo.
>> Okay.
>> So if I decide Shambo, I
could get Natalie.
>> I could get Brett and Monica
on that, no problem.
>> So that's five right there.
>> That's all we need.
Russell comes to me and says,
"If you, Brett, and Monica vote
Shambo, Shambo goes home."
But I have no idea whether
that's actually gonna happen.
>> You think it's a pretty good
move?
>> Yeah.
Anything that keeps me here
another day sounds pretty good.
Last night, I was pretty sure I
was coming back, but I wasn't
positive.
Tonight...
I don't know.
However, miracles happen
constantly.
If one happened tonight, I would
not be surprised, because the
lord freaking provides.
So Shambo tonight, huh?
>> That's how I'm seeing it.
>> Honestly, I've got no
problem with that at all.
>> Shambo's dead set on getting
rid of Dave, but, truthfully, I
don't even need Shambo.
I could let Shambo throw away
her vote, just like she did
against John, and I can get rid
of Shambo.
Yup, yup.
That's what Russ said.
>> Sure.
>> Sure. He just asked.
>> Yeah, let's do it.
>> David, they're not starting
to gun for me.
They've been gunning for me
since day one.
It's 'cause I'm the Sham with
the plan.
It's hard to compete with me.
I'll be happy watching Dave get
his torch snuffed, because that
guy drives me absolutely
bananas.
I believe what Russ says...
>> This is what's going on.
>> ...but if Dave is not voted
off tonight, I think Russ and I
are gonna be having a chat.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Erik, Kelly, Laura and John,
voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
Jaison, day 31, eight people
left, the reason you vote
somebody out tonight probably
very different from why you
voted somebody out on day two.
>> Yeah. Now I think it's more
strategic in terms of trying
to get rid of some of the
stronger players because they're
smart and are good at strategy
or because they're physically
able to win immunity.
If there's a third reason, it
would be because of the jury,
you know?
You want to have the best shot
you can, if you get to that
final two or three, whatever
it ends up being, of
getting votes.
So as far as I'm concerned,
that's probably the three
criteria.
>> PROBST: Shambo, at the last
Tribal Council, you brought up
a different reason which is, you
want to vote people out of this
game that don't deserve to go
to the end.
Still feel that way?
>> Oh, yeah, I absolutely feel
that way.
But by the same token, I
wouldn't have voted John out,
not in a million years, because
he's somebody that I was aligned
with, and I think I was more
blindsided than John was,
truthfully.
>> PROBST: Great working of the
jury, too. Well done.
>> No, this is serious.
>> PROBST: Monica, what about
somebody who's just
unpredictable and you're
getting so late in the game,
you just don't know if you can
count on them or not?
>> I definitely think that
unpredictability is scary at
this point in the game.
We're getting low in numbers,
and you want to have someone
that you know you can discuss
the vote with and realize who
do I want to see go to the end
at this point?
>> PROBST: So, Dave, what do
you have to do at this point to
stay in this game?
>> I think you've got to get
people on your side and say, "I
think you have a better shot at
a million dollars with me than
you have with this person over
here who you're currently
aligned with.
>> PROBST: Russell, Dave laid
out a very clear and
potentially effective strategy:
"You are better with me, let's
go to the end."
>> I appreciate that.
It's a good strategy.
The fact of the matter is, if
you know some people are going
to get all the votes, then you
want to get rid of them.
That's probably the most
important move of the game to
me, even more than a physical
threat.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Jaison, for the second Tribal
Council in a row, you have the
immunity necklace.
You can choose to assign it to
somebody else.
>> No, I'm keeping it.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Jaison.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Mick, you're up.
>> See you later, Dave.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
>> PROBST: If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
All right.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Shambo.
Dave.
One vote Shambo, one vote Dave.
Two votes Dave, one vote Shambo.
Dave.
That's three votes Dave, one
vote Shambo.
Dave.
Four votes Dave, one vote
Shambo.
11th person voted out, and the
fifth member of our jury...
Dave. That's five.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
Dave, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good game, you guys.
>> See you, Davey.
>> PROBST: Well, for the first
time in this game, the members
who made up the original
Foa Foa have the numbers
advantage.
No matter how bad it seems,
never count yourself out of
this game.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> I wanted a chance to play
the game.
I played my hardest.
I went full on.
Russell just played a better
game.
I think we all underestimated
Russell.
Man, he's just born to play this
game.
I'm bummed that it's over.
Now here I am.
>> PROBST: After the break,
more grudges...
>> The little bitch needs to be
sent home tonight.
>> PROBST: ...more fights.
>> Why would you do something
stupid like that?
>> I did not. I didn't do that.
>> PROBST: ...and more
betrayals.
>> Russell is Russell, so we
got to watch out.
>> That worries me that he's
going to send me home, 'cause
that's what I would do.
>> It's a no-brainer.
Well, Brett is just, uh, way too
likable.
He's a nice guy.
He would almost get 100% of the
vote, so Brett is a huge threat
in this game.
That's why I got to get rid of
him next.
>> 'Cause I remember, you know,
last night, you're, like, uh,
"Somebody's... feels like the
jury's going to like them more,
you got to get rid of them.
Somebody's a threat, you got
to get rid of them."
>> I was completely talking
about Brett the whole time in my
mind.
>> Okay.
>> It doesn't make any sense
for me not to get rid of Brett.
>> Day one, I was voted the
leader of, uh, Foa Foa, but I
think it's developed now to
where Russell is definitely, you
know, the leader of us
strategically, for sure.
I got to be thinking, he's a
game player.
He plays hard.
Maybe he's thinking of taking
other people to the jury, um,
with him so that he has a better
shot.
I'm not going to be caught off
guard.
That's the only thing.
>> Right.
>>> And I mean, I got to
wonder...
>> It makes me nervous thinking
you're nervous, to tell you the
truth.
Mick is freaking out, and when
you freak out that much, you'll
flip.
That worries me that he's going
to send me home, 'cause that's
what I would do.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready for another
immunity challenge?
>> Let's make it happen.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Jaison.
You know I'm taking it.
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you must
race out into the water,
retrieve one of your three bags
and race back.
You must then use a plank to
launch your bag into your
basket.
First person to get all three
bags in their basket wins
immunity, is safe tonight at
Tribal Council and guaranteed a
one in six shot at a million
dollars.
You guys ready to get to it?
>> Yup.
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: All right, we'll
draw for spots, and we'll get
started.
Here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Retrieving one bag at a time,
then racing back.
Jaison untying those knots.
Jaison has his first bag.
Mick has his first bag.
Brett right behind.
Russell's heading back.
Monica has a bag.
Shambo, Natalie bringing up the
rear.
You got to hop on that plank to
get your bag in the basket.
33 days.
Clearly evident.
Natalie really struggling.
Struggling just to keep her
clothes on.
Lost a lot of weight out here.
Keep digging.
Let's go.
You've been out here 33 days.
Don't stop now.
Brett gets his first bag in the
basket.
Brett heading back out on the
course.
Mick has his first bag in the
basket.
Mick heading back out.
Mick gaining some ground on
Brett now.
Russell has his first bag in
the basket.
Russell now out on the course.
Shambo gets her first bag in
the basket.
Brett, Mick, Russell, all with
their second bags.
Jaison, Monica, Natalie-- still
no luck with their first bags.
Brett back with his second bag.
Mick right on his heels.
Brett connects.
He's heading out for his third
and final bag.
Mick right behind.
It is Brett and Mick heading
out for their final bags.
Russell back with his second
bag.
>> In!
>> PROBST: Jaison has his first
bag in the basket.
Russell has his second bag in
the basket.
Natalie's now out.
Monica the only one left who has
not got a bag in her basket.
It is coming down to Brett and
Mick, both coming back with
their final bags.
Brett kicking it into high gear
now.
He's sprinting back.
Mick, you better dig.
Brett back with his final bag.
Brett can win it.
Mick for the win.
You don't want to go home
tonight.
Mick, just short.
Brett wins individual immunity!
Brett, come on over.
>> Good job, Brett.
>> Good job, B.
>> PROBST: After 33 days, Brett
does not have to worry about
going home tonight.
Mick, Russell, Natalie, Shambo,
Monica, Jaison, one of the six
of you will go home.
I'll see you at Tribal tonight.
>> Brett has shown that he's
got new life, and if he wins
enough immunity challenges, he
could put a wrench in our
entire game plan.
Now we got to get Monica, which
is fine, but this could be a
problem.
>> Thank you, my friend.
>> Baby boy, busts out a move!
>> Brett! Brett!
>> Well, finally got my time.
>> Brett, good job.
>> You didn't want to go home
today, did you?
>> I was so pissed.
I just couldn't get the freaking
thing in the basket.
>> I know.
>> We don't even got to say a
name.
We know what's up-- Monica.
>> Yeah.
>> It's done.
>> Today, Brett won immunity,
and it totally sucks for me.
At this point, it puts me in a
bad situation where I seem like
the next viable option to go
home, but I'm going to do
everything in my power to make
sure that that doesn't happen.
>> Just wondering how
comfortable you feel making it
to the final three, 'cause I was
thinking, if I was in your
shoes, I would get worried a
little bit.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> You know, you are a very
likable person, and that, you
know, obviously, can be a
threat, you know...
>> Yeah.
>> ...when it comes down to the
jury.
>> Right.
>> See, I don't know if you've
even thought about that.
>> Are you kidding me?
I've thought about it a ton.
It's like, a little kid sees a
snake, and the snake's, like,
"Hey, come play with me.
I'm not going to bite you."
And the kid starts playing with
the snake, and the snake bites
him, and he's, like, "What
happened? You said you weren't
going to bite me."
He's, like, "I'm a snake.
That's what I do."
>> Hmm.
>> So, I am very skeptical.
There is definitely a part of
me that wants to make a big move
and definitely thought about
the possibility of getting rid
of Russell.
There are emotional and moral
attachments to people, but I
mean, every night I sit there,
and I visualize in my head my
name with one million dollars
written in front of it.
So, I mean, it's tough.
>> If you want to, you know,
make a big move and, you know,
blindside someone that might
want to take you out, you have
the opportunity to do so.
>> He's a player, man.
I mean, it would make more sense
for him to take, like, Natalie
and Shambo.
>> I just don't want to be off
guard and not worry about
things, you know.
>> I'm just telling you.
I mean, you need to...
(Russell mumbles)
>> ...put people on your jury
that are going to vote for you.
>> My position is the best in
this game right now.
>> Yeah.
>> So why would I jeopardize
that...?
>> Well, I think you are
jeopardizing your game by taking
people like Jaison who's just
counting down the days to day
36, when it's your final day to
play the idol.
>> How do you think that?
>> He told me so, but I'm
telling you right now that I
did not sit in that...
>> He told me it on the beach.
He said, "Well, he can only play
that idol until day 36."
So, I mean, these are the
people you have in your court.
I'm surprised you want to put
me on the jury.
>> Yeah.
>> I can make or break you on
the jury, really.
>> Because, uh...
>> You told her I made a lot of
money?
Why would you do something
stupid like that?
>> I did not... I didn't do
that.
>> Who told her?
>> Someone else told her.
I never told her what you did.
>> How do I know?
>> Yeah.
How come all of a sudden Monica
thinks I make a lot of money for
some reason?
>> Uh, Jaison?
>> She told me what I do for a
living.
I want to know what happened.
You know, did you tell her that
you would get rid of me after I
get rid of the idol?
>> No.
>> Why would she tell me that?
>> Because she's trying to stay
in the game.
Russell was so angry.
I might have made a mistake and
told her what he does for a
living.
I honestly don't remember, but
now I'm nervous that Russell is
going to come after me, so we've
got to nip this in the bud soon.
We got to start thinking about,
you know, Russell is Russell, so
we got to, we got to watch out
because...
>> Oh, my word.
>> The three of us-- myself,
Mick, and Natalie-- we got to
make a tough decision tonight.
>> It just makes me mad and I
like it.
>> You like being pissed off?
>> Hell, yes.
Making me mad fuels my fire.
Monica, she had to run her
little piehole.
The little bitch needs to be
sent home tonight, but now I've
got to worry about Jaison, so at
Tribal Council, if I'm feeling
any kind of heat, I have the
immunity idol.
I'm gonna walk in there and if I
feel any kind of threat
whatsoever, I'll stand up and
play it.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Erik, Kelly, Laura, John, and
Dave, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
What's going on, Russell?
>> I just found a little pretty
necklace.
Thought I'd wear it, make me
look a little better out here.
>> PROBST: Shambo, is that a
surprise to you?
>> Everything he does is a
surprise.
>> PROBST: Anybody else shocked
by Russell putting on what
appears to be the hidden
immunity idol?
>> Absolutely not.
I think Russell's getting a
little cocky up in here.
>> You see, some people think
that this right here puts a
target on my back.
I beg to differ about that.
I think it puts a target on
somebody else's back.
>> He's humble.
(Monica laughs)
>> PROBST: He does have safety
around his neck if he chooses to
use it.
>> Nobody really knows what
you're gonna do with it.
That's what makes it so
powerful.
>> PROBST: Brett, things have
really changed, haven't they?
>> Yeah, I would say that, you
know, by his gestures, he feels
pretty comfortable, and as of
right now, they do have the
numbers, but when you get
comfortable in this game, things
can come and haunt you, so you
got to stay humble in this game.
>> PROBST: Shambo, what was it
like at camp after the
challenge?
>> It was probably the worst day
that we have had prior to a
Tribal.
>> PROBST: Wow.
>> Russell got his feathers
ruffled, and it was just...
It was...
>> Awesome.
>> It was not pretty.
It was ugly.
>> PROBST: Russell?
>> Monica tells me, "If you vote
me out, I ain't putting your
name down for the million
dollars, and I'm gonna talk to
everybody else; they ain't
putting your name down."
Well, you know what?
You're only making me vote you
out now because of what you
said.
>> You know, Russell came into
the merge and basically tried to
push a lot of buttons, and I
haven't seen Russell's buttons
pushed, but today he was huffing
and puffing all over camp.
"Did you say this about me?"
I mean, he was fuming, fuming.
>> PROBST: And what about that
delights you so much?
>> Basically, I couldn't help
but have a sense of pride,
knowing that if I put a
scintilla of doubt in their
minds of trust, then I
accomplished my mission.
>> PROBST: Russell, a little bit
of teacher-student.
You taught her so well, she
graduated and said, "How about
this?"
>> Seeing what I've seen today,
if I would have been on her
tribe in the beginning, we would
have been dangerous for sure.
You know, she got me pissed off,
so if she would have played that
hard this entire game, she would
be the one in charge right now.
>> Or I could be going home
earlier.
>> But I've been playing hard
this entire game and I am still
here.
>> Because of idols.
>> Yeah, well, that's playing
hard.
>> PROBST: Russell, a little
concerned that Monica could have
stirred up something that points
fingers now at you?
>> Not at all.
I know that everything is fine,
and that might be my mistake in
the game, but I don't think so.
>> PROBST: Mick, when Monica's
over there stirring it up, you
have to be going, "This is not
good."
>> Yeah, of course, absolutely,
and we're not that shortsighted
to say we're all four going to
win a million bucks, so your
wheels start spinning a little
bit.
I mean, all of a sudden, I'm
here in front of the jury with
so-and-so versus so-and-so.
You got to think about stuff
like that.
If you're not, then you're
stupid.
>> PROBST: Well, it sounds like
it was an interesting afternoon,
and the big question seems to
be: did Monica's scrambling pay
off?
Brett, you have the immunity
necklace.
I know you're not giving that
up.
>> I think I'm gonna hold on to
it.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Brett.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Brett, you're up.
>> Stupid, stupid little girl.
Bad strategy.
>> Watch out 'cause you have a
huge target on your back.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Monica.
Russell.
One vote-- Monica, one vote--
Monica.
Two votes-- Monica, one vote--
Russell.
We're tied.
Two votes-- Monica, two votes--
Russell.
Monica.
That's three votes-- Monica, two
votes-- Russell.
12th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury--
Monica.
That's four, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Monica, the tribe has spoken.
Well, there are six of you left
in this game now.
Not everybody's going to make it
to the final, so while it may
not have worked for Monica
tonight, going to be a lot more
scrambling to come.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
>> I'm in!
>> Maybe something is going on
with Mick, Natalie, and Brett.
I have to blindside everybody.
>> PROBST: With only two
episodes left, the alliances are
shifting.
>> This is the team.
Me, Jaison-- we are running the
show.
>> There's a chance that
Russell's lying to me and it
scares the hell out of me.
>> I am shocked.
I mean, 33 days, and I feel
amazing.
I think I made it really far in
this game, and I definitely went
out causing some conflict in the
Foa Foas.
I think they all distrust each
other a little bit more, and I'm
proud to say that I caused that
and that I stirred the pot a
little bit, even if it was on my
way out.