>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor...
Here in Samoa, the purple tribe,
Galu, has been on a roll...
Galu wins!
...winning all three immunity
challenges.
At camp, most of the tribe
kicked back and relaxed, while
Shambo did most of the work.
>> I'm not doing the warm and
fuzzy.
I'm doing the Rambo-Shambo
provider role out here.
>> PROBST: In a twist, Shambo
was sent to observe the other
tribe.
>> We call you McDreamy.
>> Pleasure.
>> PROBST: And she immediately
bonded with everyone.
At Foa Foa, Russell was a force
to be reckoned with.
>> I'm running this whole show
right now.
>> PROBST: He constantly
manipulated the others to
further his own ends.
>> I'm going to have them all
under control like zombies
walking around.
>> PROBST: As the yellow tribe
was preparing to go to their
third Tribal Council in a row...
>> He was...
>> If I was a girl, I would slap
you, is what I would do.
>> PROBST: ...Jaison got furious
at Ben because of his
racially-insensitive comments.
>> PROBST: Jaison wanted Ben
out, but Russell didn't agree.
>> Right now, I think I need
Ben.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Cou
Ben wouldn't back down.
>> She is from the ghetto, and
she's trashy.
That's ghetto trash.
That's not racial.
>> PROBST: So Jaison stood up to
him.
>> If what you're telling me is
that what you said had
absolutely no racial context,
then maybe you are ignorant.
>> PROBST: During the
confrontation, Russell realized
his best play was to vote off
Ben.
>> I didn't want to have to do
this, man.
>> PROBST: Ben became the fourth
member of Foa Foa to leave the
game.
Now the tribe is down in
numbers and morale.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Yeah.
>> What happened at Tribal
Council was me trying to let Ben
know how I felt.
I cannot handle people who use
terms and phrases that are meant
to hurt on a very basic level.
>> Jaison, there's room here,
too.
>> Man!
I'm hungry, and I'm tired.
I came here to have an
adventure, but, frankly, I,
right now, believe that coming
here was the worst decision I've
made in my entire life.
>> It's draining, man.
It's not only physically tough.
It's mentally tough.
It messes with your mind, your
body and your soul.
Coming back from Tribal last
night, Jaison was really upset
with Ben.
You know, he took things very
personal.
I really think that if Ben would
have stayed, Jaison would have
quit the game.
Now, what kind of man is that?
>> Yeah, dude.
>> Yeah?
>> Now I'm willing to get rid of
Jaison, and whoever I want to be
gone is going to be gone.
I've got it all under my thumb
right now.
♪ ♪
>> I got back at Galu last
night, and I'm not happy,
because when I went over to
Foa Foa, there was a huge
appreciation for Shambo, huge
appreciation.
Their camp is amazing, you guys.
Fresh water, white sand beaches.
No coral, you can go barefoot.
Everybody over there loved me.
I feel ten times closer to
Foa Foa than I do Galu, because
Galu-- they just want to lay on
the beach and gossip.
So, I don't have no problem
going to Foa Foa, because I
already have a following there,
and if I can make it to the
merge, I know damn well I've got
their vote, so I'm way ahead.
>> Yas got a clue for the
immunity idol.
>> Okay.
>> You got a clue for the
immunity idol.
>> Absolutely.
>> Wherever the immunity idol
is on their beach, it's
probably on our beach.
Nobody really got to talk to
Shambo last night about the
second clue to the immunity
idol, right?
So I come up with this little
idea to find out all the
information I want to get from
her.
(Shambo sighs)
If I can find the immunity
idol, I can give it to you if
you're in danger.
>> Yup.
>> At least you'll have that.
I'm, like, 30 seconds away from
nailing all the information I
want to get from her, and here
comes John, and he stops, and,
like, "Hey, Shambo."
Like he has this brilliant idea.
>> You got a clue, and Yasmin
had a clue.
>> I got her clue and my clue.
>> What was Yasmin's clue?
>> Yasmin's clue was, "You'll
find what you seek in the bark."
And the second one is, "It's
low to the ground."
Those were the exact words.
If it comes down to jury trial,
you guys better give me the
vote for giving you honesty on
this question.
>> Well, listen, if um...
If we can...
>> And if you don't, bad on you.
Got to go.
I don't feel like I've hurt
myself in the game in any way,
shape, or form by sharing
knowledge with them.
That can do nothing but help me
going forward.
And-And maybe it won't.
Maybe it will hurt me, but
we'll see.
>> Tree mail.
>> Uh-oh.
>> And it says, "The chief must
choose two to join him on a
quest to go on a special mission
which could turn out for the
best.
And when your chief comes
home..."
>> Oh!
>> "...your tribe might have
more to eat..."
>> Oh!
>> "...but you won't know why
until the mission is complete."
>> Basically, they just want one
guy, one girl.
We just got some tree mail, and
it says that I need to choose
two people to go on a mission,
which may or may not lead to us
having a little bit more food.
Obviously, you want to bring
people that are strong in some
sort of challenge situation.
So I'll be taking Russell,
because he is good at
strategizing, and Natalie is
good with puzzles, things of
that nature.
So I thought it was perfect.
Everybody's comfortable with
this?
>> That's fine, yup.
>> Yup, yup.
>> Let's do this.
>> Have to choose two people to
go on a quest with me, so I took
Shambo and Dave because I need
some-some brains and some
firepower.
Here comes Foa Foa.
>> So we're just sitting there
looking at each other.
You know, we're waiting for
Jeff, 'cause at every challenge
so far, Jeff has always been
there.
So we're, like, what do we do?
>> So what's going on?
>> I don't know.
>> Let's lay an egg.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Oh, my word.
>> Oh, chickens.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Who knows what's in the
other one.
>> Nah. It's probably rice and
beans.
>> Oh, if you catch the chicken,
you get the pirate chest full
of food.
Ha, ha.
>> Maybe so.
>> I don't think that's what it
is.
>> Some kind of swap?
>> I think so, too.
>> I wonder if we're just
supposed to jump, like just get
over there and start doing
stuff without even asking.
(clucking)
>> Wait.
>> A reward challenge.
"For today's challenge, you'll
be left on your own to battle
for reward inside this box... "
Suddenly, it was on.
The frenzy was on.
Shambo's grabbing chickens,
we're jumping into the treasure
box, and it's got all these
colored balls, and it's got some
instructions.
>> Oh, all right, Sham, the
reward cannot be opened and-and
shared between tribes...
Sham, put those chickens back
and come on back.
>> Hey, put the chicken back,
quick.
>> Take 'em back. Take' em back.
Take them chickens back.
>> Okay, so what is the deal?
>> Uh... "For today's challenge,
you will be left on your own to
battle for reward.
Inside this box are a flag and
three tribe-colored balls for
each player.
One player will place the flag
in the center of the beach.
One at a time, you will toss a
ball toward the flag.
The object is to land your ball
closest to the flag.
Once all the balls have been
thrown, the ball closest to the
flag wins."
>> Boccie ball.
>> It's like boccie ball.
>> It's boccie ball, horseshoes.
>> All right.
Oh, reward challenge.
Awesome!
It's basically like a game of
boccie ball.
The tribe that wins gets to
take these chickens home.
>> So, we'll start with the
chiefs, so you start first.
>> All right.
>> Yeah.
>> Then I'll start.
>> Chiefs first, ladies
second...
>> Chiefs first.
>> And the esteemed gentleman...
>> Yeah, that's fine.
>> All right, cheers.
>> All right.
>> All right, let's do this.
>> Let's go, Mick.
Oh, good shot, Mick.
>> Good job, Mick. Good job.
You got this one, chief.
>> That was a good one, too.
Ah!
>> Mm.
>> So close.
>> Wow.
>> Yes!
>> Oh, son of a...
>> Oh, God.
>> Russell's ball knocks mine
closest, and I can taste the
chicken in my mouth.
>> Wow.
>> Good shot, Mick.
>> Oh!
>> Stay out of his way now.
Make sure you don't hit it.
>> Mick had thrown those last
two balls so close to the stick.
My goal was to, like, not even
get close to him, because I
didn't want to mess anything up.
Oh, no.
Sorry, guys.
>> Nice.
>> Aah!
>> All right, you're up.
>> I'm going to knock him out
of there.
>> Get one in.
>> Mm.
>> Oop. Too strong.
>> Aim right for that stick.
>> Oh, my God, I'm a mess.
>> Try knocking his out.
>> That's what I'm going for.
>> Oh!
>> There we go.
>> Nice!
>> Nice hit.
(grunting)
>> Oh, Shannon Lee.
Lord have mercy.
>> We're panicking all over the
place.
Shambo was, like, no good.
>> Dang!
>> So now it's between Russell
from Foa Foa and Dave.
And each has three shots to win
this game.
>> All right, Russell, we need
you.
>> Good job, Russell.
>> All right, you're up, Dave.
Not bad, not bad.
>> Ooh...
>> Gosh.
>> Ooh.
>> Yes, that puts two in the
way.
>> All right, Russell, nice and
easy.
>> Don't knock anything out.
You got it, man, you got it.
>> Ooh...
>> Dear God.
>> Nice shooting, Tex.
>> That might get it done, so
you're gonna have to get at the
stick.
>> Just drop it on it.
>> All right.
>> So, Dave's got his final
ball.
We've got the closest ball to
the flag.
I'm looking over at the chickens
like I'm stoked.
This is finally gonna be
something we can bring back.
We're finally gonna win.
>> Come on, Dave, you can do it.
>> All right, so this one wins,
Dave.
>> Shh.
The last ball-- it is on me.
Make it or break it.
'Cause at this point, we are not
going home with the chickens.
>> Oh, no.
(several shouting)
>> Oh, my God!
>> Yes!
(both grunt)
Good game.
>> Good game, guys.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Good shot.
>> Thank you, man.
Thank you very much.
>> Oh, man.
It's so demoralizing.
I'm just so tired of losing to
these guys.
It totally split me in half to
see Galu walk off with those
chickens.
It's so ludicrous that we can't
even pull off frickin' boccie
ball.
♪ ♪
>> Thank goodness Russell didn't
take me to the challenge today,
because now with him gone, I can
get people doing things, working
for the tribe, while I stay home
and find that immunity idol.
>> I got ten minutes to try to
find an idol that apparently is
in the bark of a tree.
♪ ♪
(grunts)
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes!
(whispers): Oh, it's so
beautiful.
(exhales)
Of course, I'm not gonna tell
anybody I got the idol, but I'm
gonna use it down the road.
Maybe around day 30, 36.
'Cause I plan on being here for
a while, and this is gonna be my
ticket.
>> You're the man, dude.
You brought it on home.
>> Hey, man, it was your ball I
hit-- team effort, Daddy.
Seriously.
>> I'll tell you, the chickens,
they're heavy, but they're worth
every aching muscle.
Carrying that chicken coop felt
great coming home.
Every time it scraped against
the back of my ankles, I
thought, "That's okay, we're
bringing home the bacon, baby."
Do you know anything about
chickens, Shannon?
>> We need somebody who isn't
gonna accidentally let them out.
>> Yeah.
We're back!
>> You're home?!
>> We won the challenge!
>> You did?!
>> We come bearing gifts!
>> It's Russell!
>> We're bringing friends!
We're gonna have eggs every
morning!
(happy shouts, laughing)
>> We won!
>> Yeah!
>> We won! We won!
>> I won chickens.
On the inside...
We win! We win! Yes!
However, I'm just trying to stay
emotionally centered and humble
within the tribe.
'Cause getting cocky is a quick
way to show me the door.
>> Come on, guys, over here!
Come on!
>> However, I won chickens.
What did you do?
Not that. Peace.
>> All right, so this is Daisy,
Ella and Millie.
"We lay eggs and like to eat
coconut."
>> And they got to have fresh
water all the time.
>> Hey, you're on it.
I've already assigned it to you.
>> I don't claim to be a chicken
farmer, but I was introduced to
them at a very young age, and
you got to have a relationship
with chickens.
They're very finicky, they have
to trust you, they have to know
you, they have to like you.
The Survivor chickens will know
Shambo, and they will give me
eggs in turn, because I will be
kind to them.
(Shambo clucking)
(chickens clucking)
>> Talking chicken.
(clucking)
♪ ♪
(thunder crashes)
>> Mick and Natalie and Russ,
they lost the challenge.
I think normally I'd say I was
hungry for a win, but I just
want to survive to another day.
I'm tired. I'm hungry.
You know? I'm really thirsty.
So for me right now, it doesn't
really matter.
>> My true alliance, it changes
all the time.
I told Jaison I'd bring him to
the top two.
But I don't know that I can
count on Jaison to stay in the
game.
I need somebody to be able to
help me to the final two.
So I would have to take somebody
like Natalie with me.
Because she's gonna ride my
coattails the whole way.
I mean, she's too stupid to do
it by herself.
She needs me.
So I could stand up there and
say, "She followed my coattails
this whole way.
She rode me like a horse."
(laughs)
>> Day one still exists.
It's gonna be me and you in
the final.
>> That's right.
>> You're probably gonna get
upset and you're probably gonna
cry, 'cause your friends are
gonna get their hearts broken
and you're gonna be one of the
ones doing it to 'em.
>> Russell and I have talked
about, since the first day,
about being the final two at the
end, so at this point, I'm kind
of his wingman, I guess you
could say.
>> You're good... you're good
for a long while.
>> I definitely think people
underestimate me, and I want
them to think that, hey, it's
really smart for them to take me
to the end because they can beat
me.
You know, use that to my
advantage.
And if it comes down to me or
him, 'cause I know I can beat
Russell in the very end, 'cause
I would say a lot of other
people in the tribe have really
been rubbed the wrong way by
him.
So I'm just trying to not
ruffle feathers, steer clear,
build good relationships, which
is what I'm good at.
♪ ♪
(chickens clucking)
(Shambo clucking)
>> Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Escaped chicken, escaped
chicken.
9-1-1.
>> We're all kind of just
talking about that.
Everybody's so hungry.
And we hear this, "Escaped
chicken!
Emergency! Escaped chicken!"
And sure enough, Shambo let a
chicken get away.
So her and Erik, they're running
around chasing it, and it's,
like, Tweedledee and
Tweedledum.
(chickens clucking)
(squawking)
>> Erik, he's running after the
chicken, and he gets
clotheslined... by the
clothesline.
It was pure comedy right there.
>> Lynelle...
Come here, chicky, chicky.
(squawking)
(clucking)
>> Damn it.
I didn't know they could
frickin' fly.
>> I'm not calling Shambo
stupid, but it's a bird, for
crying out loud.
I would think you being a
country girl would assume that
something with wings can fly.
So yeah, I was just beyond...
just, I was stunned.
>> I don't know where she went.
>> All you have to do is look at
the chicken.
>> I said I don't know where she
went-- I'm looking.
>> She's right there.
>> Holy crap.
>> It's up in the tree.
She's so high up that...
>> There's a chicken in a tree?
>> One of our chickens?
>> I'll give you one guess.
>> Why? Why...
>> Shambo was feeding it.
>> Bingo.
>> Dude, can I just get a break?
I produce one egg, and then I
let a chicken get away.
>> Yep.
(Shambo clucking)
Shambo thinks that she's gonna
get the chicken out of the tree
by clucking at it.
Shambo tells me, "Oh, I feel
really bad, but at least I
produced an egg."
You didn't produce an egg.
The chicken laid an egg.
What did you do to produce the
egg, Shambo?
And nobody cares.
That's the worst part.
Is anybody looking for the damn
chicken? No.
That's just great.
>> Every time I try to take a
nap, Erik interrupts me.
>> Uh-uh.
>> Ugh!
Hmm.
All right, I'll be back.
>> Bye.
I am so sick of Yas doing
absolutely nothing.
She's, like, waiting around to
be taken care of like she's a
little princess, so she's kind
of frustrating and annoying.
I think the reason our tribe is
working so well is because we
are really focusing on bringing
our team as strong as possible
to the merge.
But Yas is here for herself.
She's not a team player.
She doesn't help out around
camp.
And say we do lose a challenge.
I think Yas would be the first
to go.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Galu getting your first look at
the new Foa Foa.
Ben voted out at the last Tribal
Council.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's challenge?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Brett, take back the immunity
idol.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
race across a net run carrying
wooden blocks.
When you reach the platform,
you must stack the blocks one
on top of the other.
Once you've completed the stack,
you'll make your way across a
rope bridge to another platform
where you will find more blocks.
This will stack even higher.
The first tribe to get both
stacks completed wins immunity,
is safe from the vote.
Losers-- Tribal Council, where
somebody will be voted out of
this game.
Galu, you have four extra
members-- sitting four people
out this challenge.
Who is it going to be?
>> I'm going to sit out Sham,
Laura, Dave and myself.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize, and we'll
get started.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
John out quickly for Galu.
Liz out for Foa Foa.
Got to make your way across the
net run with all of your blocks.
Everybody doing very well.
(whooping)
Once all your members are back
on the mat, you can start
stacking.
We are dead even. Go!
>> I got some big ones.
I got some big ones. Here.
>> PROBST: You're building one
tall stack.
One block on top of another.
Foa Foa working quickly.
Using the height of Jaison.
Galu starting to use a little
human pyramid action.
>> Get on my back.
>> PROBST: That's thinking.
That's teamwork.
Monica now getting up on Erik's
shoulders.
>> Come on, Monica.
>> PROBST: Can Galu make it
work?
Foa Foa very close.
Once you have it, get back to
your mat.
>> Let it go.
>> PROBST: Monica, Kelly working
together.
It's got to be there for a count
of five.
One, two...
>> We got you.
>> PROBST: Three, four.
>> Go.
>> PROBST: Five. Galu, go!
Foa Foa, one, two, three, four,
five. Go!
>> Come on, John!
>> You're way ahead.
Take your time.
>> Go, John! Go, John!
>> Stay on the rope, John.
You can do it!
>> Keep going, keep going, keep
going!
>> Let's go!
>> PROBST: John across the rope
bridge quickly for Galu.
Go!
Yasmin on the rope bridge for
Galu.
>> Go, Yasmin.
You got it, girl.
Push it!
>> PROBST: John got across very
quickly.
Jaison taking a lot more time.
Liz now on the course.
>> Good job, Yasmin.
>> PROBST: Yasmin extending
Galu's lead.
>> All right, Yas!
>> PROBST: Erik now on the rope
bridge for Galu.
>> Get across that rope, baby!
>> Come on, Liz.
Liz, you can do this!
>> Come on, Liz, keep it up.
Keep it up.
>> Good job, Liz.
>> PROBST: Mick on the course
now for Foa Foa.
Erik cruising through this, no
problem at all.
Monica on the course for Galu.
>> Let's go, Mo!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa needs to make
up some time.
Galu with a big lead.
>> Come on, Monica, you got it.
>> Come on, Monica!
Come on, Monica!
>> Go, Mick!
>> PROBST: Foa, go!
Natalie on the course for
Foa Foa.
>> Come on, Monica!
Get up there!
>> PROBST: Monica is taking a
long time for Galu.
>> Come on! Come on!
>> Keep going!
Hurry, baby, hurry!
(indistinct chatter)
(Monica panting)
>> PROBST: Natalie is making up
the lost time.
Suddenly, it's very close again.
>> Come on, Monica!
>> Come on, come on!
>> PROBST: Every second counts
in this challenge.
>> Come on, come on!
>> Damn!
>> PROBST: Galu, go!
Foa Foa, go!
>> Kelly on course for Galu.
Ashley on the course for
Foa Foa.
Ashley is screaming across this
rope bridge.
>> Come on, Kelly!
Come on, Kelly!
>> Come on, Kelly, you can do
this!
>> PROBST: Galu, go!
>> Brett, bring it on!
>> Let's go, Ashley.
Let's go, Ashley.
>> PROBST: We're down to the
last two members.
Brett for Galu, Russell for
Foa Foa.
Look at Russell go.
>> Yeah, Russell!
>> PROBST: Russell may pass
Brett.
>> Come on, Brett!
Come on, Brett!
>> You can do it, Brett!
You can do it, Brett!
>> PROBST: We are very close.
>> Go, Brett, go!
>> PROBST: Russell making up a
lot of time.
Got to get everybody on the mat.
>> We got this. We got this.
>> PROBST: Go, Galu!
Go, Foa Foa!
>> Oh! Come on! Come on!
(overlapping chatter)
>> PROBST: You've got to untie
these and then stack them just
like you did with the other
stack.
We are neck and neck.
Great competition on the rope
bridge.
Foa Foa made up a lot of time.
>> What's up? What's up?
Bring it over.
Just bring it back over.
>> PROBST: Galu has their first
bag untied.
They're going to start working
on their stack.
Galu has their second bag
untied.
Foa Foa-- still not untied.
Once again, Galu with the lead.
Looking to win their fourth
straight immunity challenge.
>> Come on, come on, take your
time.
>> You're smokin' them!
You're smokin' them!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa has their
first bag untied.
This stack will be a lot higher.
>> On my shoulder, not on my
back, Kelly.
On my shoulder, not on my back.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa has their
second bag undone.
Both tribes now working on their
stack.
>> Get it up there guys.
>> Legs locked.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa picking up
the pace now.
Natalie getting on Jaison.
Big height advantage.
We're very close.
Big, big immunity on the line.
>> You guys can see my face,
right?
>> Worry about stacking right
now.
>> PROBST: Natalie going to
stand up now.
>> Y'all, help me, help me-- all
three at the same time.
>> All three at the same time.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa desperately
wants a win.
Foa Foa loses, they will be
down to five members.
Galu with their last three
blocks.
Kelly has them.
>> Easy, easy.
>> PROBST: Natalie with the last
block for Foa Foa.
>> Push up a little bit.
>> No, I can't reach it.
>> Hurry, you guys. They're...
>> PROBST: Kelly loses two
blocks.
>> Almost there.
>> No, no, no, no!
>> Natalie, you've got it...
>> PROBST: Natalie places it for
Foa Foa!
Do they have it?
(indistinct chatter)
>> PROBST: One, two, three,
four, five!
Foa Foa wins their first
immunity challenge!
(cheering and whooping)
>> Yes!
>> Everybody keep their head
held high, head held high.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa,
congratulations.
Who wants it?
Everybody wants it.
For the first time in this
game, Foa Foa will not be going
to Tribal Council.
Enjoy the night off.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Congratulations.
(thunder rumbles)
Well, I don't know if Mother
Nature is sending you guys a
sign or not, but there's a big
cloud over your head right now.
Should be an interesting
afternoon figuring out who's
going home.
Grab your stuff.
I will see you at Tribal.
(thunder crackling)
>> I saw Monica basically
disappear at that challenge.
This is Survivor.
This is about physical, mental
toughness.
And today, Monica just did not
have it.
>> All right, so, I'm going to
try and get this fire started,
and we will, uh, keep movin' and
groovin' until it's time to do
what we got to do.
Today, we lost our first
immunity challenge, and I just
got pissed off.
That there was no reason why we
should have lost.
We had the lead the whole time,
and then I kind of saw one
person kind of fall apart, and
that was Monica.
(sighs)
>> In terms of the challenge,
Monica screwed that up.
There's no question in my mind.
>> She was terrible.
She's a young girl, hanging
out, having a good time.
It's like it's like Club Med or
something.
As much as I hate to do that.
>> Yeah.
>> What are we going to do about
the vote tonight?
>> I don't know.
>> Well, I don't know.
>> Well, I'd say that Sham's
colossal screwups are kind of a
shot to team morale.
>> Are they?
>> Well, I mean...
>> They're nonstop.
>> You know what I mean?
>> I think she does the least
out of everyone here.
>> Yup, exactly.
>> Is that where we're going--
with Yas?
>> I mean, that's...
>> As far as I'm concerned, Yas
goes.
>> We are going to our first
Tribal Council tonight.
Some names are going about.
For instance, Yas doesn't
really do anything.
She basically sits by the fire
and kind of observes things.
So that kind of gets annoying.
So I think Yas might be going
home tonight.
But, hey, it is Survivor.
Crazier things have happened.
>> You want to vote Monica out?
She took about 200% longer than
anybody to run that rope.
>> Me and John was across that
rope first and fast.
>> Right.
>> So, that's why I'm saying I
can't worry about it, because I
don't want the negativity.
>> Exactly.
>> Whatever's going to happen is
going to happen.
>> See, that's how I am.
>> I know I haven't came up
short. I'm sorry.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying?
And around this camp, I ain't
stepping up to do nothing
because you know what these
people do-- they prey on you
doing something wrong, like
letting the chicken go.
They prey on that.
>> Yeah?
>> See, so therefore, nobody
will be preying on me.
I've had my game face on since
day one.
I'm here to play.
And I did just that.
I've been running with the
fellas and helping us win our
challenges, and I'm not looking
down on nobody.
But, you know, Monica didn't
help us win today.
So if you want to penalize me
for stepping up, then so be it.
Vote me out, because my body
could use a rest, damn it.
>> Russ, to me, sounds dead set
on Monica.
>> I don't know.
I mean, I like Monica.
You know what I mean? Like...
>> There's a ton of crazy talk
about voting Yas tonight.
True, she doesn't do a lot of
work around here, but Yas is
completely stronger in
challenges than Monica.
Unfortunately, people seem to be
rallying behind Monica, and I
don't know how that's gonna play
out.
>> If you decide to go away from
Monica, then you're gonna vote
against your leader.
Which we could do, because we
have numbers, but I don't want
to be on Russ's bad side.
>> I am not in the mood to mess
with Russell.
>> Really?
>> I'm telling you, because...
>> So these people who are gonna
vote for Yas, they basically
already have an alliance,
basically.
>> Well, I don't know if it's an
alliance as much as it is, like,
a decision that maybe they don't
trust...
>> Well, they don't trust me.
You know what I mean?
That's what it comes down to.
>> Boss?
>> All right...
Yasmin, that's a vote that I
absolutely disagree with.
Every time there was a
challenge, Yasmin kicked it out.
Today Monica dragged her butt.
And right now...
That's it.
I want the strongest tribe, and
I'm the leader, so these people,
they got to listen to me, or
there's gonna be some serious
ass-kicking.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach a flame.
Dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council, because in this
game, fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire, you're
still in the game.
When your fire's gone, so are
you.
And that will be the case for
one of you tonight.
Galu gonna vote out your first
member.
Shambo, interesting afternoon
knowing you had to come to
Tribal tonight?
>> Yeah, everybody was a little
uneasy, and there was people
going for walks on the beach,
there was a little bit of
whispering going on, and...
it's not good.
We don't want to be here.
We're bummed, all of us.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about camp
life.
Brett, do you think everybody's
pulling equal share of the
weight?
>> Uh, there's definitely people
that are pulling more weight
than they should, and there's
also other people, uh, Yasmin,
that are, you know, maybe doing
a little bit less work.
>> PROBST: Yasmin, you're
already rolling your eyes.
>> I wasn't rolling my eyes, but
if you want my opinion next,
I'll be happy to give it.
>> PROBST: Sure.
>> Well, I find that a bit of a
surprise.
As a matter of fact, anything
somebody has asked me to do, I
have did it.
So I don't see how he figure I
could be doing more.
I felt like that's the
conversation him and I could've
had beforehand, and I would've
stepped it up.
Because I have not shied away
from any work.
And maybe I don't belong in a
jungle because I have on heels,
but I wanted to dress up for
you, Jeff, so I thought, you
know, that I'd look a little,
you know, nice or whatever,
so...
>> PROBST: Mission accomplished.
>> Thank you.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
challenges.
Russell, how important are
challenges in this game right
now?
>> I mean, for me, challenges
are your base.
'Cause if the base isn't there,
everything topples.
So get the challenges done, the
rest falls into place.
>> PROBST: Yasmin, you're
shaking your head in agreement.
>> I'm very competitive at
heart.
I just always like to step up,
'cause, damn it, I like to
compete.
So I totally agree with Russell,
101%.
>> PROBST: So based on what you
said, who could've given more at
today's challenge?
>> Today, Monica struggled.
That's just the way that I see
it.
>> PROBST: Monica, what do you
do when you hear your name as
somebody who might have blown
the challenge that put you here?
>> It sucks.
I mean, especially for me, I
think I did a great job at the
challenge today.
I mean, getting on the rope
originally, I had to kind of get
my bearings, but once I got past
that, I think I really came back
to my normal self.
>> PROBST: So, Dave, you can go
camp life, you can go
challenges, or you can go
individual strategy.
The problem with that is if you
start making big moves too
soon, you will destroy your
tribe and it's only a matter of
time before you're gone.
>> Uh, I think, ultimately,
what's good for the tribe is
good for me, and so that's what
I'm basing my vote on.
>> PROBST: Laura, do you agree
with that?
>> Number one for me is who's
really helping around the camp
the most.
>> PROBST: All right, well, it
sounds like there are a couple
of different philosophies about
how the vote should go tonight.
Let's see which one wins out.
It is time to vote.
Erik, you're up.
>> (whispering): I don't feel
like you have carried your
weight around camp, despite what
you say.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Yasmin.
Two votes Yasmin.
Monica.
That's two votes Yasmin, one
vote Monica.
Monica.
Two votes Monica.
Yas.
That's three votes Yasmin, two
votes Monica.
Yasmin.
That's four votes Yasmin, two
votes Monica.
>> That's five votes Yasmin, two
>> Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa, Yasmin.
That's six votes; that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Yasmin, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
♪ ♪
Well, not only did you lose a
tribe member, you guys lost
momentum.
Question is, can you get it
back?
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
Maybe the worst thing out here.
(disgusted groans)
>> ...black clouds scare me.
(thunder crashes)
>> I have never in my life been
this cold.
>> All our blankets are wet.
There's nowhere to run, there's
nowhere to hide.
>> You are lying to me.
>> Let me tell you, you're
walking on thin ice.
>> PROBST: Liz struggling to
hang on.
>> I personally feel like I'm
such a strong competitor that
had I made it to the end, it
would've been really hard not to
vote for me.
These people are going to start
to scramble, because they're not
being true to themselves.
They're tiptoeing around each
other, they're full of crap--
it's just crazy.
But you know what, if that's the
type of company I have to keep,
I'm happy to be going.