(thunder crashes)
>> JEFF PROBST: previously on
Survivor: after 15 days, the
biggest threat to both tribes
was the weather.
The Foa Foa tribe was hit
the hardest.
>> I have never in my life been
this cold, had my hands this
destroyed, and my feet look
so miserable.
>> PROBST: And while the
constant rain and cold sucked
the life out of most of them,
Russell thrived.
>> They're just a bunch
of babies.
This is really no big deal.
As a matter of fact, this makes
me stronger.
>> PROBST: At Galu, a brief
break in the rain along with
their huge 9-to-5 numbers
advantage made things a lot
more bearable.
But at the immunity challenge,
both tribes got some
shocking news:
Both tribes going to
Tribal Council.
Both tribes will vote somebody
out tonight.
(thunder crashes)
Then the brutal conditions
caught up to Russell, the
captain of Galu, who passed out
due to a combination of
dehydration and exhaustion.
There's no question to all of
us watching, brother, that, that
you are not okay.
For his own safety, Russell was
taken out of the game, leaving
his tribe without a leader.
Prior to Tribal Council, the
majority of the Foa Foa tribe
decided to send Liz home.
>> I'm putting Liz,
you putting Liz.
I know I can talk Mick into
putting Liz no matter what.
>> PROBST: While the majority
of Galu decided to send
Monica home.
>> Monica doesn't help us win
challenges at all.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
everyone's plans were put on
hold when out of respect for
Russell's traumatic medical
evacuation, the vote
was canceled.
Nobody will be voted out
tonight.
The loss of Russell re-ignited
the rivalry between the
two tribes.
>> Every bead of sweat that he
put into everything he ever
did, we're bringing that to you.
>> We welcome it.
>> PROBST: But it also provided
Foa Foa with a growing glimmer
of hope.
>> I really believe that the
tables are about to turn.
>> PROBST: 13 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Losing Russell affects
the game tremendously.
You know, losing our chief.
Losing probably the guy who I
had the most confidence in
personally in this game.
>> He played the game like he
was 35, and he's not.
>> Yeah.
>> With Russell here, we had a
5-4 gender-alliance lead,
but now with Russell gone, it's
just 4-4, and it's anybody's
ball game.
Exactly.
>> Exactly.
>> Even though she's a chick,
Shambo doesn't fit in with the
other girls.
So we have to pull Shambo back
over to our side and make sure
that Shambo is like one of
the dudes.
>> The only way that plan
unravels is if the girls lock
in Shambo.
>> Bros before hoes, period.
>> Dude.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Here we go again. Day 16.
>> Wake up, McDreamy.
Let's do it.
>> Tribal was real nice.
When Jeff said we wasn't going
to eliminate anybody, and I
knew Galu just lost big
Russell, man, I was stoked.
I was, like, "Oh, we have a shot
at this."
You know, it's 5 to 8 now, it's
pretty damn close.
>> Liz wasn't voted out, but it
keeps the tribe stronger by
keeping her.
So I'd rather just win three in
a row and then get rid of her.
>> It could be a new day.
The tides have turned.
>> That's right.
It is a new day. That's right.
>> Start with this one.
>> I'm so excited!
>> So am I.
(yawns)
>> So I was thinking
about it, thinking about it,
thinking about it, and the way
we're going to lock Shambo in
is not only to, you know, to
tell her, "Hey, we're cool with
you," but us four guys are
gonna nominate Shambo our new
new chief.
And she's gonna feel so
so important and so flattered
that she'll be as deep in my
pocket as the lint at the
very bottom.
You know, this tribe does need
a new leader.
And I think you're the best
for the job.
>> Okay.
We've got to put it to a vote,
though.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, we need to do that.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Ready? One...
>> ...two...
>> ...three...
>> ...four...
>> ...five...
>> ...six...
>> ...seven...
>> ...eight.
>> Okay.
>> So, at the count of three,
you just put up the number.
>> Okay.
>> One...
...two...
...three.
>> Okay, so wait.
How many threes?
>> Four threes.
>> Four, four.
So that's...
>> Four votes for Sham.
>> Sham's the leader.
>> Congratulations.
(man laughs)
>> I thought the way to elect
the new leader was stupid.
It went by so quickly that no
one even really realized
what happened.
Um, I don't know how Shambo got
elected leader.
And they're supposed to be
sending Shambo home last night.
I'm wondering if there was a
vote last night, would I have
been one of the people
voted for?
>> Okay, I would like my first
act of... to be one of
motivation and kindness.
I, obviously, did not ask
for this.
I will do the best I can by
you guys.
My leadership style is night
and day from Russ, and I will
honestly, honestly, honestly
do my due diligence to not be
bossy 'cause you can't really
be a sergeant in the United
States Marine Corps and not
have an expectation when you
say something, things
will happen.
>> I think us four guys plus
using Shambo as a wedge is a
good plan.
I mean, the only strategic
drawbacks I could think of is
that Shambo is just so dim that
she could screw up our plans if
we tell her anything.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
How's everybody doing?
The sun is out.
>> Very thankful.
>> Happy, happy, happy.
>> PROBST: Shambo, you're
wearing the leadership necklace.
You're the leader of Galu?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Surprised?
>> Not so much.
I've had a lifetime of
leadership skills through
just the way I was raised;
second-generation Marine, so
I just gotta keep things in
perspective and be calm.
>> PROBST: All right, we're
going to put your leadership
skills to test today.
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yep.
>> Definitely.
>> PROBST: Today's challenge
will test your memory and will
force to you make decisions
between wants and needs.
Here's how it works:
scattered out in the field
there are 13 pairs of matching
survival items.
One tribe member at a time will
walk out and uncover two items.
If they match, you score a
point for your tribe.
If at any point along the way,
the leader of your tribe
decides they would like to keep
the items you just matched, you
can do so, but you forfeit the
point in the challenge.
To make things more difficult,
four of the items are dummy
items that do not have a match.
The tribe who has the most
points at the end of challenge
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Winning tribe
will leave from here and board
a beautiful sailboat.
>> Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: You'll enjoy an
afternoon out on the water and
a nice lunch.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: In addition, the
winning tribe will send one
person from their tribe to the
losing tribe to do a little
spying until the next
immunity challenge.
You guys ready to get to it?
>> Yes.
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: Galu you're sitting
out three people this challenge.
This is a new cycle.
You can sit out whoever you
you want.
>> Kelly, Dave, and myself will
sit out.
>> PROBST: Kelly, Dave, and
Shambo.
You guys take a spot on
the bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, Shambo, since you
are the new leader and you are
not participating, who do you
want to assign to make
decisions for Galu
in this challenge?
>> Erik.
>> No, no, Brett, Brett, Brett.
>> I stand corrected; Brett.
>> PROBST: Brett will be the
fill-in leader for this
challenge.
All right, head out.
Russell goes out first for Foa
Foa, who won the rock,
paper, scissor.
That is a fire-starting kit.
That is representative of what
the real kit looks like.
It is much larger.
And rope, no match.
Cover 'em back up.
Galu. John heads out for his
first shot at this challenge.
John finds the cleaver.
Right next door, mosquito net.
No match for Galu.
Should get interesting now.
Jaison heading out for Foa Foa.
A lantern and oil.
That has not been revealed
anywhere else so it's a wild
guess, shot in the dark.
Fire starting kit.
No match.
>> That's a big break.
Big break.
>> I got it.
>> PROBST: Galu.
>> Go get it, Laura.
>> PROBST: Laura going out now.
Looking for that first match.
Laura finds one fire starting
kit.
Jaison just uncovered one.
Can Laura remember where it was?
And she does.
Laura scores the first match
for Galu.
As I said, that is merely
representative.
This is the kit.
Everything you need to get fire
started all wrapped in a tarp.
>> We'll keep it.
>> Thank God.
>> PROBST: Brett's going to
keep this one.
>> Good job, Galu.
>> Good job, team.
>> That tarp's gonna keep us
dry, right? Right?
>> PROBST: Galu scores the
first match but forfeits the
point in exchange for keeping
the item.
We're still at 0-0.
Foa Foa, head out.
Liz with her first time out on
the course would love to get
lucky.
Liz finds the cleaver.
>> Oh, gosh, Liz, come on.
>> PROBST: Can Liz remember
where the other cleaver was?
She guesses wrong, she could
reveal an item that helps Galu.
Liz reveals a mosquito net.
Not a match.
Opening the door for Galu.
Brett out on the course.
Wasted no time.
Brett finds the mosquito
netting.
Now he's got to pair it up.
And he does.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Galu with a match.
Brett, you're keeping that item
or are you keeping the point?
>> Point.
>> PROBST: Galu with their
first point.
Galu now leads one-zip.
>> Shh!
>> Liz, I gotta talk if I'm
gonna figure out where this
stuff is.
>> But we need to whisper.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa, you're up.
>> Do you know where the other
cleaver was?
it was right over here.
>> PROBST: Natalie, first time
out on the course.
Foa Foa needs a match.
>> I'm trying to decide.
>> PROBST: You're on your own
when you're out here.
You cannot get help from your
tribe.
Natalie reveals a hammock.
Natalie finds a pot.
Does not match.
This challenge not as easy as
it seems.
Lot of items out here.
It gets hard to remember.
John matches for Galu.
Galu leads 2-zip.
Russell pairs up for Foa Foa.
Laura reveals rope and matching
rope.
It is now 3-1.
Jaison reveals hammer and nails.
No match for Foa Foa.
(humming tune)
>> PROBST: Erik has a cocky
swagger.
Not a match.
Nick reveals the blanket...
Another match for Foa Foa.
No match for Galu...
Erik chooses wrong...
Brett out on the course.
And Brett matches it up.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: For Galu.
>> Good job, B. Good job, B.
>> PROBST: Mask, snorkel and a
spear goes along with that.
Brett is that an item you're
considering keeping?
>> Point.
>> PROBST: Everybody choosing
points over items.
That reward looking good.
Galu now leads six-three.
There are only three items left
out here.
The rest are dummy items that
do not have a match.
Do the math, Foa Foa.
All Galu needs to do is match
one more pair, and they win this
challenge.
Foa Foa, head out.
Natalie out on the course.
Natalie finds the pot.
She'd like to match that up,
score a point for her tribe.
>> Let's see.
Let's see.
Oh, my word.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa needs to
match this up.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Natalie matches up
the pots.
(indistinct chatter)
Foa Foa staying in it.
It's now six-four.
If Galu matches on this turn,
they win the challenge.
Monica out on the course and on
her own now.
Monica reveals the eating
utensils.
If she can match this up, Galu
wins.
And she does with confidence.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Galu wins reward.
>> (screaming): Yes!
>> PROBST: Galu, under the new
leadership of Shambo, you
continue to do very well in this
game.
Not only do you win a beautiful
reward and a nice afternoon,
you're taking back with you a
fire-making kit and a tarp.
All right, Shambo, you now have
another big decision to make.
You have to now send somebody
from your tribe over to Foa Foa,
which means they will not go on
the sailboat.
They will not have an afternoon
lunch.
They will not get a break from
camp.
Who are you going to send over
to Foa Foa?
>> I'm going to send Laura over
to Foa Foa because I need to
keep my guys strong for our
challenge tomorrow, and I'm not
sending myself for a third time.
>> PROBST: Laura, how does that
sound to you?
>> I'll take it for the team.
>> Now that Shambo's chief,
it's like she was raised in a
trailer park, married a rich
guy, and now she's driving
around in a Jaguar treating
everyone like crap, you know?
She sent Laura over to the other
tribe, and Laura's one of our
strongest females.
I don't know if she has a
strategy, I don't know if she's
just pulling it out of her ass,
I don't know.
>> PROBST: Laura will return to
Galu at the next immunity
challenge.
Galu, grab your tarp, head out.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Boat's waiting for
you.
>> Got it? All right.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa, got nothing
for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> It's just like, we just walk
away losing again, but we do
have a pox or a hex or some kind
of curse on Foa Foa.
I don't know.
I'm starting to get
superstitious at this point, you
know?
>> Hello. I'm Natalie.
>> I'm Laura. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, Laura.
>> Finally.
>> Hey, Laura. Mick.
>> Hi, Mick.
>> Good to formally meet you,
finally.
>> Good to formally meet you.
>> Pleasure.
>> I'm Liz.
>> Hi, Liz. Good to meet you.
>> Hi. How are you?
>> Good. Hi, Russell.
Good to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Welcome.
>> This is home, huh?
At Foa Foa camp, everybody is
really friendly.
Um, they're doing their very
best to make me feel
comfortable, and I sincerely
appreciate it.
>> Yeah...
I figured Shambo would send me.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah, I figured she would
send me over.
>> Hmm.
>> So... it's all right, though.
>> Yeah.
>> There's definitely an
undercurrent why Sham sent me
over to the Foa Foa tribe.
I mean... I mean, clearly, she
doesn't like me.
Oh, thank you!
>> That's for you.
>> Thank you!
>> You want to come with me and
find some crabs, show you how to
do this?
>> Yes! Absolutely.
Okay, so you have twins.
>> Mm-hmm.
I have twin girls that's nine.
My dad's a preacher.
>> He is?
I'm a theology student.
>> Really?
>> Mm-hmm.
I got my degree in women's
ministries.
>> Really?
>> I don't want to be a pastor
of men.
I don't believe that, um...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...that's the women's role.
>> Yeah, but anyway, I'm glad
you came here...
>> Wow.
>> ...and if you want to listen,
I'll have something that I can
bring to the table.
>> I'll totally listen.
>> Uh, I think, eventually, your
butt's going to be on the
chopping block.
>> Totally.
>> It might not be as fast as
mine, but eventually, it will.
But if we can get together, you
could protect me at the merge,
and I can protect you.
You know, when it comes down to
it, I hope it's final three,
'cause you know what I hope?
I would hope it would be me,
you and Natalie in the final
three.
Well, I was happy when they
decided to send Laura to our
camp, because it doesn't look
like we're going to go with
numbers into a merge, so what I
have to do now is work my
Houdini magic on Laura.
I can spot a good Christian any
time.
It's easy.
So I'm starting to really like
you now.
(Laura laughs)
>> Brother from another mother.
>> So, I'm going to start
working her, working her,
working her like a fine tool.
You know, until she's sharpened
enough just where I want her.
I swear to you, you can trust
me.
>> What are we going to do, go
to the final two, the two of us
together?
>> Final two.
>> Russell came to me and was
conspiring to have this secret
alliance that, clearly, nobody
would ever suspect.
And, you know, that's another
card that I stick in my pocket
that I might want to play.
I mean, you know, it's just food
for thought.
>> And by the way, that clue you
have?
>> Yeah.
>> You might as well throw it
away.
There's no immunity idol here.
>> Did you find it?
>> Ben found it and didn't play
it.
Hid it somewhere in the camp.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Oh, my gosh!
>> Awesome.
>> Wow!
>> The reward was phenomenal.
We're on this rowboat, headed
toward a pirate ship in the
middle of the islands of Samoa,
and honestly, I just felt like I
don't even deserve that, you
know?
Like, what have I ever done in
life that has been so great that
deserves that kind of an
opportunity?
(applause, indistinct chatter)
>> Are we helping, or are we
watching?
>> Uh, you're doing both.
>> Excellent.
>> Yay!
Yay!
>> Haul away!
>> Haul away, come on!
(whooping, indistinct chatter)
>> Yeah, get it E!
>> Use your youthful exuberance
of the purple team.
>> That's the spirit!
(laughter, indistinct chatter)
>> Ahoy, matey!
>> Come on!
(whooping)
>> You have to turn the wheel
to the right.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Wait!
(screams and whoops)
(whooping)
>> I'm a sailor!
>> A pirate ship!
>> You're, like, the captain of
a pirate ship ready to go rob
some booty.
(laughter)
A little gold, a little
wenchin', a little groggin'.
A little more wenchin'.
Uh-oh, look what's coming out.
Oh, baby.
>> Oh!
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Yay!
>> Yes!
They fed us this beef stew that
was delicious.
It was almost all meat and a big
chunk of handmade bread and
these amazing scones.
They were delicious.
I was having a good time, man.
>> This is so beautiful.
What a nice change after 16
days of hell.
My God! Thank you, Lord.
>> And I appreciate you
not sending me.
Shambo ended up sending Laura
to the other camp.
I think it just was her own
little way of saying, "I'mn
"leader now, and what
I say goes."
I mean, she'd never admit that.
>> I didn't relish the thought
of sending anybody over there,
but I'm also not gonna feel
bad about it because I think
that I did the right thing by
the tribe, I really do.
♪ ♪
>> I would've never guessed
that in a million years.
That's cool.
>> As long as we have
a flame...
And I was just, like, "Yeah."
>> You know, I understand we
have a guest.
You know, Laura's come here to
hang out with us until the next
immunity challenge, but I don't
really need to hear her and
Natalie talking about the
spiritual book of, you know,
spiritual book of the month,
like, behind my back, when I'm
trying to get a fire started so
that we can eat and drink.
>> Whoo! I'm going get my hands
washed.
Do you need to do any kind of
laundry or anything?
>> Oh, gosh.
>> It's just really infuriating
because they're not helping.
It's time to start a fire.
All they're doing is sitting
there picking their toes and,
like, catching up on good times.
So it was really, really
frustrating, disappointing, and
at times, rather infuriating.
This is like a crisis, and
they're talking about their
faith and books.
Russell, I understand we have a
guest, but they're talking about
book-of-the-month club.
>> Yeah.
>> Damn!
>> Liz is so stupid.
I don't even see how she can
walk without falling down.
It's just ridiculous.
If we merge, we need somebody
on the inside, and Natalie's
doing a good job talking to
Laura around the camp.
So I have to keep Natalie for
my little toy.
You know, she has to be there
for me so I can manipulate her
little mind and do what I want
her to do.
When it comes to this game, you
better be street smart, and Liz
has a mouth on her, and I don't
think she knows when to shut up
so I'm going to keep my eye
on her.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, Laura,
you can now rejoin Galu.
Galu is back intact.
You guys ready to get to
today's challenge?
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first,
Brett, take back immunity.
Thank you.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, both
tribes will paddle out to
retrieve fish-shaped
puzzle pieces.
Once you've collected all six
sets, you'll then paddle back
where three tribe members will
use those pieces to solve
a puzzle.
First tribe to get it right
wins immunity;
safe from the vote.
Losers... Tribal Council;
somebody going home.
Galu, last challenge it was
Shambo, Kelly, and Dave Ball
who sat out, so you three have
to participate.
Who are going to be the
sit-outs, Shambo?
>> It's gonna be, uh, John,
Monica, and Laura.
>> PROBST: All right, before
you go, though, Mick, where's
the leadership necklace?
>> Uh, well, we left it back,
actually.
We were, uh, halfway wondering
if maybe it was bad luck.
>> PROBST: But you still have
a leader?
>> Yes, absolutely.
>> PROBST: All right.
As long as you have a leader,
the necklace is merely symbolic.
we will see if that is the
difference.
Laura, Monica, John, take a
spot on the bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize,
we'll get started.
Here we go.
Galu hoping to continue
their dominance.
Foa Foa hoping that necklace
was, indeed, bad luck.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Three people paddling,
two people fishing.
>> Hop in, Erik.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa using
the height of Jaison to
still push their boat.
Foa Foa starting to pull
away now.
>> Dave, hop out!
Guide us, guide us!
>> I'm up an out!
>> PROBST: Galu now getting in
the water trying to push
their boat as well.
Natalie has one for Foa Foa.
>> Here you go, here you go.
>> Right there!
Bring it to you.
>> PROBST: Dave Ball has the
first one for Galu.
>> Right here.
>> Come on, Liz.
There you go.
Pull it up.
>> PROBST: Liz has one for
Foa Foa.
Foa Foa moving on to the second
station.
>> Come on, you bitch!
Come on! Oh!
>> Nice job, Liz!
>> PROBST: Liz hooks the third
set of puzzle pieces for
Foa Foa.
>> There you go. There you go.
>> All right, Natalie.
>> PROBST: Natalie has the
fourth set!
Foa Foa off to an early lead!
>> Come on, Dave, you can do it.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> You got it right here, Dave.
>> PROBST: Dave has the second
set for Galu.
>> I got it! I got it!
You just push! You just push!
>> PROBST: Liz snags the fifth
fifth set.
Foa Foa has one set left!
>> All right.
I need to concentrate.
I need silence, please.
>> You can do it, Dave.
>> Be quiet!
>> Come on, baby.
>> Yeah, I got it.
>> I gotcha. I gotcha.
>> PROBST: Dave has the third
set, Kelly has the fourth set
for Galu.
>> All right, we're going.
Move it!
>> PROBST: Liz and Natalie
circling that last set of
puzzle pieces.
That last string of puzzle
pieces.
>> Get it! Get it!
>> PROBST: Liz has the last
string of puzzle pieces for
Foa Foa!
>> Push! Y'all push!
>> PROBST: Better start
heading back!
>> Push!
>> Get on it, both of you!
>> Quiet!
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Kelly has the fifth
set for Galu.
>> Good job. You got it.
>> Right here, babe.
>> PROBST: Dave has the sixth
set for Galu!
Galu now heading back.
>> All right, Galu!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa has one
paddler and two swimmers.
>> Good job, good job.
>> PROBST: Galu trying to push
their boat as well.
A lot more work to swim it than
it is to paddle it.
>> Brett, get in the boat now!
>> PROBST: Galu now getting
the boat.
Everybody paddling.
>> Full paddle forward!
>> Paddle!
Paddle!
>> PROBST: Galu now using all
their paddlers and they are
gaining on Foa Foa.
>> Stroke! Stroke!
>> PROBST: Foa Foa getting it
done without Jaison!
Foa Foa's hooked in.
Get back to your mat.
Galu's hooked in.
Get back to your mat!
(groaning)
>> Set up time!
>> Come on. Come on, push, push.
>> PROBST: You can start
working on the puzzle any time
you like while other
people untie.
Liz working on the puzzle for
Foa Foa.
Dave, Kelly, Brett, working the
puzzle for Galu.
Jaison, Mick, and Liz working
it for Foa Foa.
>> Here's the last one.
They're going to make a
line, yeah?
>> Shh!
>> Liz, I gotta talk to
somebody, all right?
Stop shushing me.
>> PROBST: Look for
the patterns.
Something to help make
sense of it.
>> Look at the colors.
Match the colors.
>> We are, we have! Look. See?
>> Yeah, that's...
>> PROBST: Jaison frustrated.
You can't give up.
>> Can they fit like this?
>> Like this?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Every single inch of
this may not be filled
with fish.
There may be gaps in
this puzzle.
That may be part of the pattern.
>> PROBST: Foa Foa thinks
they're on to it.
Galu starting to get a pattern
pattern going.
Follow that pattern.
If you've got it, follow it.
>> Here you go, good job.
>> PROBST: Galu starting to
pull away now.
Jaison, Liz, and Mick
struggling to keep in this.
>> Goes like this.
Yeah, like that.
>> PROBST: Galu thinks they have
have it.
Galu wins immunity!
(all cheering)
>> Yeah, baby!
Right on!
>> Whoo!
>> PROBST: Galu, once again
immunity is yours.
Well, Mick, it looks
looks like it wasn't
the necklace.
>> We had the pattern, I think,
before they did.
We just couldn't get the pieces
together quick enough.
You know, again, it's
frustrating.
>> PROBST: All right, Foa Foa,
once again Tribal Council
tonight where one of the five
of you are going home.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> These idiots are probably
gonna cost me
a million dollars.
I planned on having a lot of
fun with the money,
a lot of fun.
Maybe we need to get rid of
Jaison because he gave up
out there.
He's just standing there
looking at the puzzle like it's
gonna move itself.
We gotta mix something up, so
what happens, happens.
♪ ♪
>> This whole time I wanted to
get rid of Liz, get rid of Liz.
But you know what?
Jaison gave up when we were
pushing the boat, and then he
was so tired, he couldn't even
get up there and do a puzzle.
It's amazing to me that he
can't, you know, get these
puzzles down.
I don't know.
He's sure not going to be my
attorney.
How in the world are they
beating us in puzzles, Mick?
>> I don't know.
>> Jaison went...
You went to medical school,
Jaison when to freakin' Oxford,
Stanford.
>> I know. I know. I know.
I know.
>> Gee!
>> I can't explain it, my
friend.
I cannot explain it.
>> Agreed.
>> You know, like, when you lose
so much, all you want to do is,
like, go into, like... crawl
into a hole, fetal position?
That's how I feel.
>> Quite embarrassed.
>> I don't get it.
We were ahead, too.
I just don't know what... how
we... why we always lose our
lead.
>> I have no idea what's going
to happen in this vote tonight.
I did not perform well in the
puzzle, I don't think.
You know, I couldn't get with
the program.
I kind of felt like dead weight
to the team.
So, for all I know, they could
be voting me out.
Well, sorry about my performance
on the puzzle.
I couldn't figure that thing out
to save my life today.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm trying to concentrate on
putting it behind me.
Hope tomorrow's a brighter day.
>> Okay.
>> Okay, these are the two
options.
Now, I've been thinking about
this.
Natalie, for sure... or...
>> Yeah?
>> ...Jaison.
>> I know.
>> Now listen why.
>> He's been dragging his feet
lately.
Yeah.
Yeah, go back.
>> With tonight's Tribal
Council, my survivor stock has
gone up because I certainly
thought the vote would be
between me and Natalie, just
because we're physically, you
know, smaller, weaker, than the
three guys, but I guess,
strategically, you know, it may
make more sense for Jaison to
go, and I'm actually quite
thrilled because I never would
have anticipated that.
>> You know, I got a decision
to make.
It's going to have to be either
Liz or Jaison.
The thing is, with Liz, I don't
know if we can trust her once
the merge happens.
But the thing is with Jaison, I
still think I can trust the
guy, but, you know, we still
got to think about winning in
challenges.
We're losing with the team we
have.
We've got to find some way to
win.
Something has to give.
>> PROBST: Well, there's no use
going over the dismal facts.
Losing eight out of ten
challenges, or the fact that
after tonight, you'll be down to
four members, while Galu holds
strong at eight.
One of the worst overall
performances of any tribe in
the history of the game.
Natalie, what I want to know is,
where is the attitude on this
tribe?
Still hanging in there?
>> Absolutely.
It doesn't do any good, uh, to
get negative, so we have to go
in to any challenge with our
heads up, because if we don't,
then we're done, so...
>> PROBST: Russell, do you still
wake up every morning and think,
today's the day?
>> Yup, every morning.
All we really can do is hope for
the merge 'cause they outplayed
us.
They're outlasting us.
But one thing I promise you--
them kids over there-- there's
no way in hell that they can
outwit me.
>> PROBST: Liz, if you get to a
merge, do you trust these guys?
>> Absolutely.
There is no doubt.
After all these Tribal
Councils, I absolutely trust
each and every one of these
people up here with me 100%.
>> PROBST: Mick, any doubt in
your mind about the
trustworthiness of this group
of people?
>> Honestly, Jeff, none.
The performance aspect-- we
haven't done great, obviously.
But there's still a social game
to be played, and that trust is
at the absolute core of our
survival, and we all know that.
>> PROBST: So, Russell, being
this tight, got to be hard to
vote somebody out again tonight.
>> It is very hard.
You know, five people down to
four people.
You know, it almost seems
hopeless, but if we can just
keep that four together, then
you'll see.
You'll see exactly...
The whole thing's gonna change.
>> PROBST: Jaison, since we got
here, you've been like this all
night.
Occasionally popping your head
up.
What's the hardest part about
this for you?
>> I am frustrated with losing,
is really what I'm frustrated
about.
And I actually do feel like I
have some large responsibility
in these losses.
You know, today in the puzzle.
You know, I feel like Mick did
a really good job figuring out
what the pattern was.
I think Liz had the pattern
going, but I just couldn't
figure out how to see the
pattern at my end, and so, I
don't feel like I performed at
a level at which I should have.
>> PROBST: So if you're voted
out tonight based on today's
performance, would it be fair?
>> If they decide that, you
know, my performance today
warrants me to walk away, I hope
that that is what is necessary
for them to win tomorrow.
>> PROBST: All right, it is
time to vote.
Mick, you're up.
>> This is totally strategic
and not at all personal.
Sorry.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Jaison.
Liz.
One vote-- Jaison, one vote--
That's two votes Liz, one vote
Jaison.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa-- Liz.
That's three. That's enough.
You need to bring me your
torch.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Liz, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, you haven't been very
successful at challenges, but
you're getting really good at
blindsides.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
(indistinct chatter, cheering)
>> To our new tribe.
>> New tribe.
(whooping)
>> All of a sudden, all hell
breaks loose.
>> Monica needs to go home
tonight.
>> It's Erik 100%.
>> I got to do what I got to do.
Things are going to get crazy
tomorrow out here.
>> This experience was...
It was nothing but intense.
My tribe mates outwitted me.
It was a very strategic move,
and the tables turned so quickly
that, you know, it's a little
bit surprising, but kudos to
them.
I really, really hope that they
make it to the end.
And this is one hell of a game,
so I'm glad I made it as far as
I did.