>> JEFF PROBST: Galu making a
big move now on their puzzle.
Previously on Survivor...
Galu wins immunity!
Since the start of the game,
Galu has won almost every
challenge, and they seem
invincible, but cracks are
starting to show.
The four guys formed an
alliance and ticked off the
women by electing Shambo their
leader.
>> I thought the way to elect
the new leader was stupid.
>> PROBST: And there's a feud
brewing between Shambo and
Laura.
>> Clearly, she doesn't like me.
>> PROBST: On day 16, Galu won
yet another reward challenge.
Galu wins reward!
So Shambo stuck it to Laura by
sending her to Foa Foa for a
short visit...
>> All the way.
>> PROBST: ...and denying her a
once-in-a-lifetime reward.
>> I think it was her own little
way of saying, "I'm leader now,
and what I say goes."
>> PROBST: At Foa Foa, Russell
and Natalie immediately pounced
on Laura.
>> Natalie's doing a good job
talking to Laura around the
camp.
If we merge, we need somebody
on the inside.
>> PROBST: When Foa Foa lost
another immunity challenge...
Galu wins immunity!
... they went to Tribal Council,
and Russell made good on his
threat to knock out Liz.
>> You're the weakest link when
it comes to trust.
>> PROBST: Liz, the tribe has
spoken.
Outnumbered eight to four,
Foa Foa now needs a miracle in
order to survive.
12 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> So tomorrow if we got to go
get it...
As a tribe, we're down to four
people, so we're in a horribly
inferior position to the Galu
tribe, and so it makes our job
even more difficult, 'cause we
got to try to struggle to get to
a merge and then try and divide
and conquer.
Otherwise, we're all screwed.
>> What is that, 12 people left?
>> So it's a possibility the
next thing is a merge.
Yeah, when we get over there,
dude, the game on.
>> Game on.
>> The game starts.
If we all stick together and all
talk to somebody different, man,
at least one of them's going to
work for us.
>> Yeah.
>> You know?
Foa Foa needs a merge.
We have some strong ideas once
we get over there.
We plan on working as a team,
talking to different people.
>> There's segregation in their
tribe.
In our tribe, Foa Foa, there's
unity.
We're all working as a team, so
I'm not really nervous about my
numbers.
I'm too good for this game.
I'm too sly, and now I've got to
make sure my seed is planted in
all of these dumb asses' heads.
So once we do merge, we can stir
them up over there.
♪ ♪
>> Since my return from the
Foa Foa tribe, seems like
there's definitely a lot of
tension.
I mean, clearly, Shambo doesn't
like me in camp.
And that was a huge reason why
I got sent over to the Foa Foa
tribe.
>> Yeah, that makes nine, and
that means there's one
somewhere, because I brought it
back.
Do you want to take my canteen
until we find it?
>> I have no reason to lie to
anybody.
>> I wasn't accusing you of
lying.
I was just asking where the
canteen was.
>> Laura, for two or three days,
you've been coming at me.
If you want to take a walk with
me so we can sort things out,
I'm good with that, but if you
don't, it's okay.
>> I don't need to work
anything out.
I don't know what's going on
with me and Shambo.
When I got sent over to the
other tribe, Dave handed her my
canteen.
I didn't care.
But when I came back to camp, I
said, "Where is it?"
And then, she makes this huge,
big deal, and then, all of a
sudden, brings up all these
other things that I have no idea
what she's even talking about.
>> There's some, like, little
power struggle going on between
you and I, and I don't get it.
I don't understand it.
I don't like it.
It's like there's this 90210
little young thing in you going
on, and, uh, it-it's just...
it's bizarre to me.
>> Now, how you perceive that,
if your feelings get hurt, and
if you're, like, "Well, what's
her problem?," well, that's on
you.
>> It wasn't a fight about
canteens.
It really is the way that she
treats me on a regular basis.
It's almost like those popular
girls in high school that are
cheerleaders that want to snob
their nose at people that don't
fit into their circle.
I'm done with her.
I have no use for her, none.
>> You have a way of turning
things about, so, like, now I
look like the bad person, like I
blew this whole thing up, like,
"Where is my canteen?
Where is my canteen?"
>> They're totally arguing over
nothing, absolutely nothing.
Totally pissed off at nothing.
Fantastic.
>> So my feeling is, so now I
have to suffer.
I'm without a canteen.
>> To be honest, we know
Shambo's crazy, so if you get
in a fight with Shambo, who's
the one who looks bad?
You look bad.
You fight with Shambo, that
means you're just as crazy as
her, only you're not really
crazy.
You're just being a bitch.
>> "It's time to follow your
leader.
Face to face with your rivals
once more.
With your bodies pumped, and
your minds sharp, your taste
buds and stomachs can score."
Oh, that would be awesome.
>> Sooner or later, something
has to change for us.
I'm hoping today is the day.
We're not super confident in our
ability to win challenges
anymore, uh, but we just don't
want to lose any more immunity
challenges, 'cause the four that
we have is the four we want to
go into a merge with.
They're the people that we think
can really, really help us out
when we get there.
>> We got tree mail.
It's so vague, we don't really
know what it really means.
I mean, it doesn't sound like
the merge, but I'm pretty
confident it is about to happen,
so I have to take my immunity
idol everywhere I go.
We only have four people now,
but we have such a tight group,
so it's not over.
There's so much more to this
game than playing a physical
game with somebody.
You have to be able to outwit
them.
That's the most important thing
of the whole game.
>> We were going to the
challenge.
We were walking down the beach,
the other tribe's coming down
the beach towards us, and we're
meeting at this treasure chest.
And Jeff isn't around, so
everyone's kind of on edge, not
really sure what's happening.
(overlapping chatter)
(whoops)
>> Nice!
>> I'm so excited.
>> "Congratulations, Foa Foa
and Galu.
You are now one tribe."
(applause and cheering)
(laughter)
Good job.
>> New buffs for everyone!
>> "You will all go back to live
at the old Galu camp.
Take some time to get to know
your new tribe mates.
A feast awaits you down the
beach."
(screams, cheers and chatter)
I can't even tell you the sense
of relief that I felt reading
that it was the merge.
I no sooner got those words out
of my mouth that I just knew it
was going to be a hell of a
good day.
(screaming)
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh... my... God.
(screaming, overlapping chatter)
>> I'm actually really, really,
really happy that we merged, and
the feast was delicious.
There was chicken, all seasoned
and roasted.
There were cheeses and fruits.
>> Look at the size of these
grapes!
>> Oh!
>> Mmm!
>> It was, like, literally a
feast fit for royalty.
>> To our new tribe.
>> To our new tribe!
(whooping and chatter)
>> To Samoa.
>> Cheers!
>> Galu-Foa Foa merge.
I am on top of the world, man.
I'm in heaven right now.
You guys, these are lemon
meringue mini pies.
>> This is what we've all been
talking about.
>> I am on such a sugar high
right now, I'm, like, "My
prayers were answered totally."
>> Uh, yeah.
Got a mechanical engineering
degree.
>> Congratulations.
>> Like, at first, I thought
"These hermit crabs are great,"
but after about seven or eight
days, I'm, like, "I never want
to eat another one of these
things."
You know what I mean?
>> Russell is the best crab
catcher, though.
>> Things are about to change
totally in this game.
The other tribe-- I don't think
they even realize it right now.
>> I'm not bad, right?
I'm not overbearing?
>> I'm looking around at Foa Foa
when everybody is taking that
step to do exactly what we said
in camp.
>> I'm a good snuggler.
>> Get with these people, bring
them under your wing and connect
with them.
>> It was a good day.
>> We're steps ahead of them.
We already have our plan down.
>> Cheers.
(laughing)
>> The ones I know I can trust--
they're doing exactly like I
want them to do, and it's going
to get stronger as we go along.
>> I can already see that I'm
the ruler in this kingdom.
>> Got it?
>> I mean, come on.
Who gets grapes fed to them?
The kings do.
>> This is it!
>> Our new home, buddy.
>> Welcome, you guys.
>> Thanks for having me.
>> Do y'all have a certain place
for bags, and....?
>> Now we got some more body
warmth, too.
>> That's our kitchen.
>> Oh.
>> This is what we call the
cutting board, or the kitchen
sink.
>> Y'all are, like...
The Galu camp-- I love it.
It's awesome.
I feel like I'm at the Hilton.
You know, at Foa Foa, we had
absolutely nothing.
Here at Galu, there's blankets,
pillows.
Everybody-- it really seems
like a family.
>> I'll show you where our
water and stuff is.
>> Okay.
Laura kind of took me under her
wing.
She was kind of like mother hen,
showing me around, and it was
really nice, because it was
really important for me to talk
to Laura to find cracks in this
group.
Make no mistake, there are
cracks.
It's just, are there enough
cracks and big enough cracks to
get the numbers on our side?
>> We got to pick a name.
Does anyone have any suggestions
or ideas?
>> Slow-mo?
>> Does anybody have any funny
Samoan slang?
>> Aiga is, uh, Samoan for
extended family.
>> Cool!
>> What is it? Aiga?
>> Aiga.
>> That sounds good to me.
>> I like Aiga.
>> All in favor of Aiga, say
aye.
>> Aiga.
>> Aiga it is.
>> That's it.
>> No, I like it.
>> That's all I get.
>> Foa Foa-- the only thing that
they have going for them is they
have a new beach, and they have
new people to talk to.
They're starting over.
They're on day two.
I'm on day 19.
I have the hidden immunity idol.
It's in my pocket.
And that's power in this game.
And they think that they're
going to strategize and make
friends, and la-la-la, we're an
extended family.
Like, the name of our tribe,
Aiga, means extended family.
Ugh!
(laughter)
Extended family?
What's Samoan for "Get the hell
off my island?"
>> I definitely have tricks up
my sleeve.
Day one at Foa Foa, I was very
aggressive.
I went to everybody right off
the bat, and my plan happened.
It happened like I wanted to.
Over here, I'm going to go to
people, saying the same things,
doing exactly the same strategy,
but I have the idol to be able
to make them sway my way.
>> Obviously, I didn't find this
on the beach.
It's the real deal.
Now, if you could take me to the
top seven, I'll hand it to you.
I'll give it to you.
I swear I will.
>> Okay.
>> Nobody.
Everything's between me and you.
>> Okay. So top seven?
>> Top seven, I'll hand it to
you.
>> I can't believe Russell
showed me he had the idol.
But you know what?
Desperate people do desperate
things.
I don't believe he would give
that to me, but just knowing
that he has it is huge, which
means when we do get rid of
him, it's going to have to be a
big blindside.
>> There's a few rules that I
want to put in place with this
deal.
You can get rid of my guys
whenever you want, but the first
one to go has to be one of your
guys.
>> That won't happen.
>> You don't think?
>> Who do you want the first one
to go, one of my guys?
>> It'll be one of your guys or
Shambo.
>> Right.
>> It's kind of funny.
Russell came to me with this
attitude of, like...
"I'm the boss, and here's some
rules," he tells me.
And I'm, like, "Okay, well, just
so you know, I kind of hold all
the cards right now, and, um,
you just need to try and stay
alive."
You're in a worse position than
myself at this point.
You're coming here with ten
percent.
I got 90.
>> Right.
Laura's digging her own grave.
She told me, "I'm 90% in charge
of this, Russell.
You're about ten percent right
now."
In other words, sit down and
listen.
No.
It don't work like that for me.
Okay.
She might be the first to go.
All right, well, I'm just going
to try to win them all, then.
(Laura laughs)
What else can I do?
I went to Laura.
I thought it wasn't going to
really work, so I'm going to do
the same thing with somebody
else.
Maybe, uh... uh...
Monica.
>> ...I would give this to you
and let you use it.
>> I'm in.
>> Okay.
This has to stay between me and
you...
>> Absolutely.
>> ...or this won't work.
Monica didn't mean a word she
said over there on the rocks.
I see it in her eyes, but she
might actually start meaning
what she tells me if I get rid
of her boss.
I get rid of Laura, she comes
a-runnin'.
Now, if we can get one of the
guys on my side, that would be
gold.
I'll get rid of Laura one way
or the other.
>> That's crazy.
>> I got it with no clue.
>> That is impressive, bro.
>> I'm telling you, dude, we can
be in control of this game
without them even knowing.
I can convince my people to vote
whoever I say.
I know you can do the same.
>> Mm-hmm. Right.
>> Dude, I swear, if I think
your butt's on the line, I don't
have a problem giving it to you,
and letting you use it.
>> And then we'll keep driving
it, yeah.
>> You're the only one here that
can do it with me.
I see that.
>> Russell divulged to me that
he had the hidden immunity idol.
I think because Russell's an
aggressive player, and he
realizes that maybe having a
relationship with someone like
me is something that could be
very, very beneficial to him in
this game.
>> Do you think Laura is
trustworthy?
>> What do you think?
>> I think she should go first,
'cause once she's gone, the girl
power is over.
>> Yeah.
Laura and Monica have a
relationship that is potentially
dangerous.
And even though it's going to be
viewed as a big move, I think
it's a manageable risk to vote
off Laura first, while we have
votes from the other tribe.
>> My guys are going to vote
Laura.
Right.
>> Then I'll go get some
cavalry.
That's crazy, bro.
>> And then it could be me and
you at the end.
>> That is crazy.
>> Me and John could be a good
team, I believe.
He's smart enough to know what's
going on, so things are going to
get crazy tomorrow out here.
>> All right.
>> We're going to turn this game
on its side.
>> Hey.
>> Shake your hand as a man.
>> Absolutely.
>> This is... I'm a...
I'll be...
I'll honor what I say right now.
>> Absolutely.
>> You ever heard of a man named
Babe Ruth?
He struck out more than anybody
ever.
But you know what?
He also hit the most homeruns,
so that tells me one thing.
Keep swinging, baby.
Eventually, you're going to hit
one.
(laughs)
>> No, I'm using a-a snail.
Shambo's a really good person,
and we do connect.
I think it has a lot to do with
my Southern background.
People trust the South.
So she could be one of my
numbers.
I mean, I could use her for
that.
>> Of course I am.
Knowing what a little spiteful
snake she is.
She's half the battle.
>> We got in quite the little
scene.
She was just being a bitch to
me.
I said, "What is your problem?
You've been very, very
mean-spirited and just, you
know, awful to me."
>> Wow.
Shambo hates Laura.
She hates her.
So I know at any point, she'll
vote Laura's name.
You know, get rid of a strong
player, Laura, and get rid of
the snake.
>> I trust Russell implicitly.
The guy is definitely cut from
the same cloth as me.
He's a country boy.
I'm a country girl.
And he just keeps bringing up
that Laura needs to go first.
She's the bane of my existence
in Samoa.
So, it's not like we need this
multi-layered plot.
Write Laura's name down tonight.
It's that simple.
You need to make sure that you
have the conversation.
Pull Jaison off to the side.
>> Pull Mick off to the side.
>> Pull Natalie off to the side.
>> And tell them, "No matter
what, Laura is the only name we
are writing down." Okay?
>> Sounds good to me.
>> Outstanding. Carry on.
>> It was easy to control these
minds.
Way easier than I thought.
John's on board, and I have
Shambo in my pocket.
So if we can get rid of Laura,
this whole game might change.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You have now merged into one
tribe.
It's a completely different
game.
You guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> Yeah.
>> Dave, I'll take back tribal
immunity.
Now that you're merged into one
tribe, tribal immunity is no
more.
Individual immunity is what you
covet.
When you are wearing this, you
are safe at Tribal Council.
Let's get to the challenge.
Today, you'll participate in a
game of good, old-fashioned
Survivor T-ball.
It's very simple.
>> Sweet!
>> PROBST: One at a time, you'll
place your ball on the tee, take
a swing.
Whatever section your ball lands
in, you score that many points.
Highest score wins immunity.
And for today's challenge...
there are two necklaces.
(low whistles)
>> PROBST: Because two people
will win immunity.
The women will take on the
women.
The winner gets immunity.
The men will take on the men.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
Dave Ball, you're first up for
the men.
>> Let's go, Dave.
>> Go, Dave.
>> Let's go, Danger Dave.
>> Ugh!
>> PROBST: Danger Dave.
Baseball your sport?
>> Uh, no, making love's my
sport.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: You play a lot?
>> Not often enough.
(laughter)
>> Geez.
>> Let's go, Dave.
That a boy.
>> PROBST: Nice swing.
Where's it going to drop?
>> There you go!
>> PROBST: Pops into the three.
>> Go, Dave.
>> PROBST: Not a bad score.
>> Dave-O.
>> Good job, Dave.
>> PROBST: Jaison now up.
Three is the mark to beat.
Got a chance.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: On and off the course
for Jaison.
Jaison, you cannot win immunity.
(applause)
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Russell's up.
Dave's still the mark to beat
at three.
Russell gives it a ride.
>> Nice, Russ.
>> All right, Russ.
>> PROBST: Lands it in the four.
>> Nice.
>> Oh, man!
>> PROBST: That puts Russell in
the lead.
>> Good shot.
>> Good job, Russell.
>> PROBST: Brett is up.
Russell has four, which means
you have to land in a five or
the ten up in the sky.
That might do it.
>> Aw!
>> Nice try, Brett.
>> PROBST: And off the course.
>> Good shot, baby.
>> PROBST: Brett cannot win
immunity.
>> That was a good hit.
>> Go, Mick.
>> PROBST: Mick is up.
Russell still in the lead at
four.
Mick needs to get something in
the four to five range here.
That won't do it.
Mick scores two.
>> Ugh!
>> PROBST: That's not enough.
Mick out of this challenge.
Erik, take your swing.
Russell still in the lead with
four points.
>> Going for the ten, baby.
>> PROBST: Going for the ten.
>> Let's go, Erik.
>> PROBST: All the marbles.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Oh! A nice swing.
Just off the course, though.
Ends up zero.
>> Good swing, though.
>> You looked good.
>> Thanks.
>> Yeah, at least you looked
good.
>> PROBST: John.
>> All right.
>> PROBST: The last person.
Russell is one person away from
winning immunity.
Russell with four, which means,
John, you have to land in a five
or the ten to win immunity.
John gives it a ride.
Nicely done.
John lands in the five.
>> My God!
(applause)
>> PROBST: John wins individual
immunity.
>> Nice one, John!
>> Holy crap, Johnny!
>> Good job, John.
>> PROBST: All right.
The women are now up.
Natalie, you're first up for
the women.
>> Oh, man.
>> PROBST: Natalie down and
hard.
It bounces out of the course.
(all groaning)
No score for Natalie.
>> No! Nat!
>> Oh, goodness!
>> PROBST: Monica's up.
Another lefty.
Monica, nice swing.
>> Girl.
>> Oh, God.
>> PROBST: Ends up in the two.
Monica scores two.
>> That a way, baby.
>> PROBST: Kelly, you're up.
Two is the mark to beat.
>> Oh, good job, Kelly.
>> PROBST: Kelly.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: With a three.
>> Good job, Kel!
>> PROBST: That puts Kelly in
the lead.
Shambo's up.
>> Let's go, Sham.
>> PROBST: Three is the mark to
beat.
Big swing.
>> Lovely.
>> PROBST: Little result.
>> Outstanding.
>> PROBST: No score for Shambo.
Laura, you're up.
>> Score.
>> PROBST: The last person.
Kelly-- still the mark to beat
at three.
You're going to need at least a
four to win immunity.
Laura lands it in the four.
Laura wins individual immunity!
(applause)
>> Good job, Laura.
>> You did good.
>> PROBST: Laura, John, come on
over.
Congratulations.
(applause)
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
John and Laura cannot be voted
out at tonight's Tribal Council.
As for the rest of you, one of
you going home tonight.
Should be an interesting
afternoon for the newly-merged
camp.
By the way, what is your name?
>> Aiga.
>> PROBST: Aiga.
All right, Aiga, grab your
stuff, head back to camp.
See you at Tribal.
>> When I saw Laura win
immunity, I got a gut-wrenching
feeling in my stomach.
The plan had been put into
motion.
We were going to write down
Laura's name tonight, and now we
can't.
So, that sucked, because I
really wanted her gone.
>> Thank you.
>> They can't win anything.
>> No. No.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know 'cause I haven't
talked to anybody yet.
>> I'm getting rid of the girl
thing.
>> Well, dude, that ain't going
to happen.
>> You don't think?
>> No.
The problem is Erik and Laura--
they will decide who will go
today.
If that means that we will lose
a number on your tribe, we lose
a number.
>> Laura would definitely be
gone, but she won immunity
today, and Shambo-- she don't
want to get rid of Monica.
She says that's not going to
happen.
She wants to let one of our
guys go.
I'm sure I'm being targeted, so
I don't want to have to play the
idol, but if I'm feeling antsy
about tonight, I might have to
go that route.
>> Yes.
>> Uh-huh.
I know he has it.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Damn it!
He thinks he's going to go
first, so I bet you he's going
to play it tonight anyways.
>> Yeah. Yeah...
>> Perfect.
>> So the fact that he has it
seems kind of dangerous.
>> I know, I know.
>> We all know that. I know.
Listen. Listen to me, listen to
me, listen to me, listen to me.
This morning it was supposed to
be Laura.
Laura won immunity, saved Laura.
The next best thing that you can
do to weaken Laura is to ax
Monica.
Some members of Galu-- they just
want to go down the line--
Foa Foa, Foa Foa, and it's like
they're playing really junior
varsity Survivor right now.
There are tons of inherent risks
to breaking up the team that
we've worked this far to develop
at Galu, but it's a risk I'm
comfortable with, because I
still believe that it's in our
best interest to get rid of
Monica.
>> I can calm her down.
>> But you keep her at bay, you
keep her at bay.
>> I can calm her down.
You know, at first I didn't like
the idea.
However, by allowing me to vote
with Laura, when she gets
spooked after Tribal Council,
she'll have nobody to turn to
but me, and I can go ahead, gain
her trust, which could be good
for me down the road.
>> Are we gonna use Foa Foa?
>> We are?
>> Yeah.
>> Here's what needs to happen.
A: nobody talks to Shambo.
Period.
>> Perfect.
>> Let her vote whatever she
wants.
>> Okay?
>> If you go Monica, Monica,
Monica, it's done.
>> Yeah.
>> Erik-- he wanted to vote
Monica, which is crazy.
The plan to just vote Foa Foa
and shoot them down, you know,
turkey shoot-- pop, pop, pop,
pop, so there may be something
going on in Erik's head that
he's not letting on 'cause he's
a crafty, crafty dude, and that
makes me a little nervous.
(buzzing)
>> ...then definitely the three
of you will stay, and I'm pretty
sure Russell will stay, anyway,
so...
We want him to think that he's
going home tonight.
That way, he plays the idol.
So, what you need to know, you
know.
You choose a different route,
there will be a different
outcome, I can't guarantee the
four of you are here tomorrow.
>> Here's how I feel right now.
I feel like Erik is talking ...
to the tribe.
>> Erik told us that if we get
Russell to flush out the idol
and use it tonight, they will
agree to vote out one of their
own, um, instead of one of us,
but to be honest with you, I
don't really like that guy.
So I kind of want to just put
four votes on Erik and-and let
the ball roll.
>> I don't know who...
>> But I could leave this game
easily, knowing that he went
before me.
>> Why is he freaking out?
>> He wants all of the girls
gone.
>> I don't trust Erik.
>> He was... Here's the thing.
>> Well, because there's no way
to pull it together.
Like, we can ask Kel.
>> Okay, okay.
>> Okay, Kel.
>> The thing of it is, like,
Galu still has plenty of people,
plenty.
I'm telling you, y'all, he is
going to wreak havoc.
Kelly and Laura-- I just
basically let them know that
Erik needed to go now.
We have four people.
They have eight.
It's not a big deal if they lose
one.
I'm definitely putting my faith
in Laura and Kelly, and I'm just
going to hope that it works.
>> What?!
>> He's trying to get you off
tonight.
>> Are you serious?
>> Yeah.
>> Really? Everyone's on board?
>> He's manipulating everybody.
>> Yeah, I know, but...
>> Tonight Erik goes.
>> Who's Erik?
>> Erik.
>> Our Erik?
>> Yes.
>> Wait.
>> This is the first time that I
don't know nothin'.
All of a sudden, all hell breaks
loose.
All the girls want to vote Erik
out now.
I don't know what they're
thinking.
They could possibly be saying,
"Hey, let's say, vote Erik.
That way Russell will feel way
comfortable, won't use his idol,
we'll vote him out."
And then, they get me and the
idol.
>> This is like going to Vegas.
>> Yeah.
>> What else can we do?
They blindside one of us, we go
home, we eat pizza.
>> What concerns me is that it
just seems almost too easy right
now, and that makes me
uncomfortable.
Fortunately, I got my idol in
my pocket, and I'll use it if
need to use it.
>> PROBST: Jaison, take me
through the merge.
Foa Foa's already down to four
people.
Now you have to go over to
Galu's camp where they've been
living this whole time.
>> I mean, it's almost as
frustrating as-as losing
challenges, you know?
But at least with the
challenges, we had some say in
it.
So for me, a guy who is used to
having at least some control
over his life, I think more than
even frustration, you just feel
helpless.
>> PROBST: Monica, how does this
merge change the trust in the
game?
Before it was, can I trust the
people on my tribe?
Does it suddenly become, I have
to trust the people on my tribe?
>> In this game, you never
really know who to trust.
I mean, someone could be saying
something to your face, and then
saying something completely
different behind your back.
So even though Foa Foa is down
in numbers, someone could turn
their back on you.
You just really never know.
>> PROBST: Erik, looking at the
four Foa Foa, what do you think
Galu should base the vote on?
>> You know, to me, I struggle
to see anything that Foa Foa has
to offer Galu.
Let's just say that they were
able to get a Galu member to
turn in a very cohesive team, I
would be floored if I saw them
get one, let alone two or three
that they would need to actually
spin this game.
And that's not me being cocky or
confident.
But I just struggle to see what
it is that they can do, you
know.
Your heart goes out to them,
but, you know, they're in the
hole.
>> PROBST: Russell, Erik's
saying, "You don't offer us
anything.
Why do we need you at all?"
>> Well, I don't like pity.
I think that we have a lot to
offer, and I think he's going to
be surprised.
>> Again, you see the tenacity
in the eight of us since day
one, so it's a long shot.
>> PROBST: But can you
understand why somebody who's
down in numbers, like Foa Foa,
would do anything to try to stay
alive?
>> I think one way to look at it
is, how is it that they've
reacted to the merge and
mingling with us?
I'll tell you right now-- Russ
goes out there and scrambles.
He's been in everybody's ear.
Uh, Mick comes in, he does his
thing, he takes it on the chin.
He says the numbers are what
they are.
Natalie doesn't want to step on
anybody's toes.
And Jaison is-is just an enigma,
because you see this
intelligence, and you see this
physical prowess and his
athleticism, but you don't
really see it come together.
>> PROBST: Jaison, basically
saying you got great potential,
but not doing anything with it.
>> Um, you can take a look at my
résumé.
I'm here to play a game.
I'm here to be strategic in my
own way.
So, I have a strong, strong
problem with that... with that
comment.
>> I mean, you want to talk
about résumés, let's look at
your résumé in this game from
day one.
You know, I'm thinking you're
making my point.
>> Honestly, the personal
attacks on me in which someone
says I can't put it together
just-- they-they eat at me.
You know, for 28 years, I've
been fighting to-to do things,
to accomplish things, and I feel
like people have doubted me the
entire way, and I've had to
push through roadblocks that I
couldn't go around or under or
over, and so I think maybe it
just takes me back to those
days.
And I've tried to play this
game hard, but not take it too
seriously, but sometimes, you
know, something just kicks in,
so...
>> Well, I like that.
You know, I like that in a
player.
If I was your coach, I would say
that's what I like to hear.
>> I guess the point is that I
don't care what you like.
>> PROBST: Russell, there's a
lot of judgment coming from Galu
to the Foa Foa group.
Are you feeling a little
attacked or maybe misunderstood?
>> No, not at all.
You know, we can still make this
happen.
This... We still have hope.
>> PROBST: So, Erik, you got
to respect Russell saying, "I
don't care that we're down to
four.
I still believe I can win this
game."
>> I do respect the fact.
He does not strike me as someone
who gives up.
I respect that.
But this type of competitiveness
is misaligned, and if he doesn't
focus it within the next couple
of days, if it's repairable,
then I can't say 100% I respect
it.
>> In other words, just roll
over and get voted out quietly.
Well, that ain't going to
happen.
I will talk to each and every
individual up here, and I'll
try to strategize with everybody
to try to stay in this game.
I ain't going to stop playing.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
John and Laura, you both have
individual immunity tonight.
If you want, you can assign that
immunity to somebody else.
>> Never in my life, Jeff.
>> I'll keep it.
>> PROBST: All right, you cannot
vote for John.
You cannot vote for Laura.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Dave, you're up.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
>> Everybody knows I have it.
I might as well play it.
>> PROBST: The rules of Survivor
state that if anybody plays a
hidden immunity idol, then any
votes cast against that person
will not count, and the person
with the next highest number of
votes will be voted out.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Russell
tonight will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Jaison.
Jaison.
Two votes-- Jaison.
Erik.
One vote-- Erik.
Two votes-- Jaison.
Two votes-- Erik.
Erik.
That's three votes-- Erik, two
votes-- Jaison.
Erik.
That's four votes-- Erik, two
votes-- Jaison.
Erik.
That's five votes-- Erik, two
votes-- Jaison.
Erik.
Six votes-- Erik, two votes--
Jaison.
Seventh person voted out of
Survivor: Samoa, and the first
member of our jury-- Erik.
That's seven.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good, B.
>> PROBST: Erik, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, your first vote as a new
tribe, first blindside.
This is most definitely a new
game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
>> Russell, Natalie,
Mick, Jaison.
>> PROBST: The old Galu declares
open season on Russell.
>> Russell is the most conniving
player in the game right now.
He needs to go.
>> PROBST: And now he's out of
idols...
>> It was the dumbest move,
playing that idol.
>> PROBST: ...low on friends...
>> It's got to be Russell.
>> PROBST: ...and in need of
luck.
>> This is the first time that
I'm struggling on what to do.
>> Wow. Wow. Wow.
I'm disappointed, but I said
playing Survivor would be
looking into a mirror, and I'm
pretty proud of the face I see.
I don't regret going home with
the idol, 'cause you can't
defend against something that's
invisible, and this blindside
was invisible to me.
But I gave 100% of my heart, and
I can hang my hat on that.