>> JEFF PROBST: The South
Pacific.
Thousands of islands
lay scattered across the world's
most beautiful ocean.
But for centuries, man has
traveled these waters to meet
in combat.
From brutal tribal warfare to
the the epic battles of World
War II, this is a place where
rivals have long traveled to
settle old scores.
It is the perfect setting for
our biggest showdown yet.
Welcome to the 20th season of
Survivor.
Over the past ten years,
Survivor has traveled to some
of the most desolate,
dangerous and exotic places
in the world.
(bird calling)
Over 300 people have tested
themselves in the most
difficult and groundbreaking
show on television.
We have gathered 20 of them to
play one more time.
These are ten of your favorite
heroes...
versus ten of the most
notorious villains.
>> In my world, I've always
tried to show that good
will win.
>> I'm a villain.
I think villains are smarter
than heroes because they don't
mind stabbing somebody in the
back to get where they want
to get.
It's a fact.
It's a proven fact.
Google it.
>> The Heroes are definitely
people I would rather play the
game with.
The Villains are the people
I've always been against.
So this is perfect for me to be
on the heroes' side and battle
it out against these punks I
don't like anyway.
>> I've been labeled things
like "She-devil in a blue
bikini," "The wicked witch of
the West."
"Man-eater Manthey"-- that was
my favorite one.
(chuckles)
>> I'm back here to do what I
came to do the first time-- get
to the end and make the money.
So I'm definitely coming back
to redeem myself.
>> This time, I slay everyone
and trust no one.
This is my chance for
redemption.
>> I'm not in the shape I was
last time, but I still think
that I could hang in there as
tough as any guy next to me.
>> But these people are
smart, they'll get rid of me
right right away.
It's the smartest thing they
could do, but they won't.
They never do.
>> I'm almost a decade older
than I was the first time.
So to me, it's a test to see if
I still got it.
>> Last time I was mean, and
this time I'm meaner.
You know, I'll lie.
I don't care.
But I'll make up a good lie.
>> People think they know me.
They really don't know me.
(laughing)
I'm a gangster in a Oprah suit.
But I'm not, like,
a mean gangster.
I'm a nice gangster with a
smile, you know.
>> PROBST: it is still the
ultimate challenge:
20 people forced to work
together while battling the
elements and each other.
They must learn to adapt or
they'll be voted out.
In the end, only one will
remain to claim the
million-dollar prize.
39 days, 20 people,
one survivor.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Flying in the choppers, my
heart's beating a mile a minute.
I'm sitting right next to Tom
and Cirie and all these people.
I know the game's going.
I'm finally back in the game.
>> Flying in on the helicopter,
you can feel something
in the air.
There's an electricity.
There's a tension.
There's a level of excitement
that is coursing through
everybody's veins,
especially mine.
And to start off like that, I
think sets a great tone for how
the season is gonna be.
>> Believe it or not, I'm a
little nervous going in.
I'm still in awe of who I'm
here with.
I mean, for God's sake,
Boston Rob...
Parvati.
I mean, you know, I gotta
get my mind straight and not
let them get me too starstruck.
I'm out here playing a game
with them now.
>> I'm nervous and I'm excited.
And, you know, like before you
bungee jump or something, you
get that knot in your stomach,
and it, like, makes you want to
throw up, kind of?
That's how I feel right now.
>> I look over and see my
fellow tribemates with the blue
buff on getting out of their
copter and running over.
It's pretty intense, you know?
My tribe, the Heroes tribe,
they're hard-working, you know,
tough guys, good people.
I was like, you know,
"This is it."
I can't wait to kick some
ass out here.
♪ ♪
>> Here we are, we're on our
nice little blue mat, and then
here come these Villains, and
you see, you see Boston Rob,
and he's already got the whole,
the walk and the swagger and
the attitude.
And then, you know, you see
Coach and Jerri.
I mean, they really
are villains.
>> Yay!
I'm the original villainess of
Survivor and I gotta tell you
I feel like Mother Teresa right
now with these people.
(laughs)
It's on.
>> PROBST: All right, let me
officially welcome you to
Survivor 20: Heroes vs.
Villains.
(laughter)
>> Yeah, baby! Whoo!
>> PROBST: Ten years, 20
seasons, over 300 people have
played Survivor, the greatest
adventure game in the history
of television.
Russell, how does it feel to be
deemed one of the ten most
notorious of all time?
>> I'm still in awe that I'm
here with...
with all these great players.
Finally, I can play the game
with somebody that respects
the game.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob, you
proud to be seen as one of the
ten biggest villains
of all time?
>> I'm a villain?
(all laughing)
Well, it's all in
perspective, I guess.
It's how you see it.
>> PROBST: Rupert, a lot of
people have played this game.
>> Yup.
>> PROBST: You're still, to
this day, one of the
most popular.
>> Uh, it's, it's been
an honor since the first time
that I got to play.
And now when I found out I'm on
the Heroes' side, I tell
you, I love the game, and being
able to have this chance,
it's, it's an honor.
>> PROBST: Tom, another big
hero, played a very solid game.
A lot of people like you.
They were happy you won, which
isn't always the case with some
of our winners.
Stack up these two tribes.
>> You know, we kind of got
maybe some positive energy
going just 'cause we've been
labeled the good guys, but, um,
I also wouldn't assume that
anybody would stick with the
game-play that they had.
If it didn't work for them in a
previous season, I would say
that they might do a 180 on this
thing and spin it around, and I
think that could be from
either tribe.
>> PROBST: Colby, in your
season, Survivor: Australia,
our second season,
going back almost ten years
ago, you were so popular, people
were naming their children
"Colby."
(laughter)
>> Most of the ones I heard
about named their dogs "Colby."
(laughter)
So a kid's not bad.
I'll take that.
>> PROBST: What's the
perspective now, almost
ten years later?
>> It's taken me almost this
long to really get enough
perspective to appreciate it,
and this is, this is my third
time back, and it is,
it is humbling.
It's the experience and it's
the adventure.
If you're not fired up at this
point riding in on those
birds, you don't have a pulse.
>> PROBST: J.T., is it at all
intimidating, even within
your own tribe, when you
look around at who's
surrounding you?
>> It's definitely intimidating.
I watched these people
when I was in high school.
I was too young to apply for
the show, so I couldn't do it,
and now I'm out here competing
against them.
And I'm still a rookie out here.
I'm probably the youngest one
out here.
I feel like a young kid against
these people, but I'm ready.
>> PROBST: Anybody out here
feel they are on the wrong
tribe, legitimately feel
they're on the wrong tribe?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> What'd we do?
>> Yeah, what did we do?
>> What did we do that was
so bad?
>> PROBST: So pretty much every
Villain thinks they should be
on the Hero tribe.
(laughter)
Except Jerri Manthey, the
original black widow, still
owning her title.
>> I even got a black hat for
this season.
>> Is there a little symbolism
with her hat being black and
mine being white?
>> PROBST: Good versus evil?
>> It was not a mistake.
>> PROBST: Parvati, let's be
clear; while you did a great
job and were rewarded with a
million dollars, you led one of
the most notorious tribe of
women ever in the history
of the game.
You betrayed people left
and right.
You guys were responsible for
many, many blindsides.
Great player?
Yes, that's why you're here.
Hero? No.
James, from your two cents--
Parvati, hero or villain?
>> Villain.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: James is bigger
than me.
James is right.
>> I will fight him.
I'm not scared of him.
(laughs)
I don't care how big you are.
>> Uh-huh.
>> PROBST: Anybody here willing
to say that the sheer size of
James does make them take pause
for a moment?
>> Yes.
>> I don't want to wrestle him.
>> Hello?
>> PROBST: James, anybody on
the Villain tribe
intimidate you?
>> It's the same story every
every time.
The talkers are the most
dangerous.
The ones who strategize are the
best ones at the game.
They-- bar none-- have won most
of the series, most of
the seasons.
>> PROBST: So you've learned
something in your two times
out here.
>> Believe it or not, I have.
>> PROBST: Going back to
when you were voted out with two
idols, one in each pocket.
(James laughs)
>> Yes, thanks for reminding me.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob, how big
a factor is size versus scrap?
>> I-I think that we have a huge
advantage over them.
Our women are clearly stronger
than their women.
And our guys can hold the best
of it.
>> Yes, yes.
>> I'm being serious.
>> You got the gloves, Jeff?
>> I don't see how they're
gonna be able to keep up
with us.
I love you, Colby, but, man,
you got the raw end
of the stick.
>> I'm so glad he's here.
I'm so glad Rob's back.
>> PROBST: So, Rob, nobody on
this tribe of Heroes
intimidates you?
>> I didn't say that, Jeff.
I just said I think that we have
the advantage.
And we're not gonna be busy
dealing with all the egos
over there.
>> PROBST: All right, well,
we're gonna see how you
match up right now.
It's time to get to your first
reward challenge.
Here's how it works: you will
square off two-on-two.
On my go, both pairs will race
out to dig up one bag.
Once you have the bag, you must
race back to your finish mat.
That's where it's gonna
get physical.
You have four people battling
for one bag.
To score a point for your
tribe, you have to be touching
the bag and your finish mat at
the same time.
First tribe to score three
points wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Well, in addition to
the challenges being physical,
the conditions are gonna be
demanding as well.
Between the heat and the rain,
if you do not stay hydrated,
you will not last long.
Fire for the winner of the
first challenge.
Having fire ten minutes into
this game gives you a huge
advantage going into that first
immunity challenge.
You win that challenge, you
have momentum, you could ride
that all the way to the end.
I know it's worth playing for.
I'm gonna give you a minute
to strategize on your matchups,
then we'll get started.
All right, let's get to our
first challenge.
The first matchup is going to
be Stephenie and Cirie for the
Heroes, taking on Parvati and
Danielle for the Villains.
This is the lane you're going
Right where I am.
Just come to me.
Survivors ready?
Go!
There's one bag in this sand.
You've got to find it, and
you've got to get back
to your mat.
Danielle and Cirie did this
challenge in their season,
Exile Island.
They're now opponents in the
same challenge.
Cirie has the bag.
Cirie and Parvati going at it.
And it's physical quickly.
Danielle trying to steal it
from Cirie.
>> Come on, Danielle!
Hold onto it, Danielle!
>> PROBST: Stephenie and
Danielle now have it.
Parvati now has the bag for the
for the Villains.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Parvati takes it back
from Stephenie, but Stephenie
takes Parvati down.
Cirie in on it.
Cirie now and Danielle.
Cirie is like a linebacker in
this challenge.
Parvati working Stephenie over.
>> Come on, Danielle!
>> Come on, Parvi!
>> PROBST: Danielle has the bag
for the Villains!
Villains score the first point!
Villains lead one-zip.
>> My shoulder.
Wait, wait, wait.
>> No. We got medic. He's here.
>> No, no, no.
Hold on, hold on.
I gotta relax.
>> PROBST: What happened?
>> If it's out...
>> What do you want me to do?
>> I'm a medical student, and
when I saw Stephenie dislocate
her shoulder, I knew she could
leave the game permanently over
something like that.
>> PROBST: You want medical
look at it?
>> What happens if medical
looks at it?
>> PROBST: Stay here, stay here.
Medical.
>> Ah!
>> Hi.
>> PROBST: Her shoulder's
popped out.
>> Yeah, we'll get her down.
You can just kneel down for
for me?
(Stephenie gasping)
Hold it up.
>> PROBST: Hold it up?
Like that?
>> Yup.
Just need someone to go
over there.
You're all right.
>> PROBST: Hang tight, okay?
(Stephenie gasping)
(crunch)
>> Oh! Okay.
>> Yay!
>> The Villains are brutal.
They dislocated my shoulder the
first challenge.
I mean, really?
Like, you're already on the
Villain tribe, do you have to
act like a total, like, jerk?
It's okay now. I just...
>> PROBST: Wow.
>> All right, guys, let's go.
>> PROBST: All right, we have
played our first point of the
first challenge of
Survivor 20, and we have
our first injury.
Stephenie's shoulder had
to be popped back into place.
Next round is one man,
one woman.
It's Amanda and J.T.
taking on Randy and Jerri.
Lane two.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Jerri!
Kick some ass!
>> PROBST: Looking for that bag.
then you gotta get back
with it.
Everybody putting one hand in
the sand and one eye on their
their opponent.
>> Randy!
>> PROBST: Jerri's got it.
Now, it's a battle to get it up.
Jerri found it, but she didn't
get it up.
Amanda trying to pull Jerri out
of there.
>> Get right on him, Randy!
Pull him down!
>> PROBST: Randy and J.T. going
at it.
>> Jerri, get back down!
>> PROBST: Nobody has the bag!
>> Punch him!
Punch him, punch him!
>> PROBST: J.T. has Randy in
some kind of a hold.
That's some country right there.
All that work and the bag is
still stuck in the sand.
>> Jerri, behind you!
>> PROBST: J.T. trying to get
to get it.
J.T. has the bag!
Randy get on him!
It's one-on-one!
J.T. eludes Randy.
We are tied, 1-1.
Here we go, next round, it
is Colby and Tom taking on
Coach and Russell.
You're coming to lane nine,
the last lane.
Survivors ready?
>> You guys got it, you got it.
>> PROBST: Go!
Russell digging for the
Villains, Tom and Colby digging
for the Heroes.
Coach hanging back,
just watching.
Not gonna let anybody get a
free sprint to the finish.
A big matchup; four
strong guys.
Four fit guys.
This will not be an easy path
to get back to your mat.
Whoever gets this point is
gonna earn it.
>> Russell's got it!
>> PROBST: Russell has the bag
for the Villains.
Tries to toss it to Coach!
Doesn't work!
Colby now has a hand on it!
This is full on.
Coach takes Colby over.
Colby's trying to push
Coach off.
Coach not having it.
>> Hold your bag, Colby!
>> Get on your feet, Tom!
>> PROBST: Colby inching
forward.
>> Drag him up!
>> PROBST: Russell now trying
to get free of Tom.
Colby ready to make a move.
>> Leave his crotch alone,
Coach!
Okay, Colby!
>> Come on, Russell!
>> PROBST: Colby now dragging
Coach.
(Tom groans)
Russell really being tough on
on Tom.
Play fair, down there!
>> Come on, Tom!
>> PROBST: Colby eyeing that
that mat.
>> Come on, Colby!
>> PROBST: He's just got to make
sure coach doesn't drag him to
the other mat.
>> Keep it up, Coach!
>> PROBST: Coach now dragging
Colby.
Here comes Tom and Russell!
Coach scores for the Villains!
(Colby gasps)
>> Colby getting owned by Coach?
Oh, my gosh, dude.
I can only imagine what
Colby's thinking.
He's got to be, like, "I may as
"well just become a woman,
"because there's no point on
"trying to maintain my
masculinity now."
>> PROBST: Villains now lead
2-1.
Next round.
We are back to women
taking on women.
It is Sugar and Candice for the
Heroes taking on Sandra
and Courtney.
Lane five.
Survivors ready?
You're in the right lane.
Heroes need to score.
All four women are digging and
watching at the same time.
Trying to find the bag while
making sure somebody else
doesn't find the bag while
you're looking.
>> Courtney got it, Sandra!
>> PROBST: Courtney had it.
>> Sandra, get up!
>> PROBST: Candice is holding on
to it.
Courtney fighting in there.
The smallest woman in this game.
>> Candice, stand up!
>> PROBST: Candice now trying
to get up.
>> Hold onto her!
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
>> PROBST: Candice standing up
but Courtney pulling her
back down.
>> Come on, Courtney!
Hold on! You gotta hold on!
>> PROBST: Candice dragging
Courtney toward her mat.
Sandra has Sugar.
>> Come on, Sandra!
>> Go, Sandra!
>> PROBST: Sandra now getting
involved.
>> PROBST: Sugar trying to take
that bag from Candice.
>> There you go!
>> Sugar, get up!
>> Get up, Candice!
>> PROBST: Sugar has it.
The bag is now free!
The bag is totally free!
Sandra undid Sugar's top.
That bag is free, and nobody
can get free to get it!
Sugar lets go of her top.
Sugar takes the bag!
Sugar gives up vanity and
scores for the Heroes.
>> Initially, I thought maybe
Sandra shouldn't be on the
Villain's tribe.
Not anymore.
Sandra earned her title as a
Villain for me with the bra
incident and Sugar.
>> PROBST: We are tied: Heroes
two, Villains two.
Playing to three.
This is it.
For the Heroes, James and
Rupert, taking on Tyson and
Boston Rob.
This should be a doozy.
Come to me right here.
Lane eight.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Hey, hold up!
Make James work! Stay back!
>> Stay away from 'em, Rob.
>> PROBST: James digging.
Tyson digging.
Rupert digging.
Boston Rob is just sticking
back and watching.
Tyson has it for the Villains,
but James ties him up before he
can even get it out of the sand.
>> Good job!
>> Hey, hold up!
>> PROBST: Rob now going
for the bag!
>> Stay back!
>> Stay away from 'em, Rob.
>> Go, Rob!
>> PROBST: Rob and James going
at it.
>> PROBST: Rupert ties up Boston
Rob.
It's James and Rob.
Rob tries to take James, can't
do it!
James scores!
Heroes win reward!
>> When I came out of that final
heat, my toe, instead of going
up and down, went like a "J."
My toe is broke.
>> Oh, my God.
>> I can feel it.
Not that one, this one.
>> We'll fix you with codeine.
(Rupert gasps)
>> There we go.
That's stuck in now.
>> My toe is broke, and I felt
it cracking inside.
But I'm not getting put out of
this game over a damn toe.
First damn day.
>> PROBST: All right,
so let's do an injury count.
Rupert has a broken toe,
Stephenie has a dislocated and
then relocated shoulder.
Hopefully, it was worth it.
Big victory for the Heroes.
Fire.
And a map to your new home.
Villains, you are definitely
living up to your name.
Grab your stuff, head to your
camp and start working on
on shelter.
>> The Villains lost.
You think that really bothers
me, losing?
'Cause I'm used to losing with
a bunch of dummies.
But the difference is this
ain't a bunch of dummies.
We will win.
And I'm looking forward to
sending the Heroes to Tribal
Council and letting them do
their hero thing.
>> Look what we've got here.
We've got fins.
>> Fins, and is there a sling
in here, or not?
>> Fins!
>> There's a...
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> What?
>> You gotta make your own out
of a stick.
>> Make it.
>> I can't believe I'm doing
this again.
It's just starting to sink in.
I believe I'm going to have to
stay on my toes with these
fellas.
I'm ready for it.
I'm ready for the challenge.
>> I think that we should live
under this tree because it's
it's dry.
>> That's what I'm,
that's what I'm thinking.
This is, like, the biggest tree
right here, right?
>> I am, yeah, really bad.
>> Really?
>> I got about ten bites
already.
>> They like that dragon blood.
(laughter)
>> I got way more to prove
right here than I did the
last time.
If I could do it here, if I can
take it all the way, if I can
whup these all-stars, doesn't
that mean I'm the best ever?
>> I'm gonna play similar
to the same game.
I'm gonna use the mind game.
They better give it their all
and play the game because
I'm taking this crap serious.
That's why I'm here.
I have to work my magic on,
on the villain side, which is
gonna be tough.
I'm gonna be straight up
with you.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, so do I.
>> I'm an aggressive player.
I'm here to win, and, you know,
I want to make smart alliances.
>> The thing is, if we can
trust each other and we can do
this... which I trust you.
>> Yeah.
>> ...which, I trust you.
>> Yeah, I trust you, too.
>> You have to trust me.
You have to no matter what.
>> I know.
>> Because that's the whole name
of the game.
>> I know, I know.
>> And this is where it happens
the first day.
This is when it happens.
>> Sure, I know.
>> With Russell, he's a great
person to play this game with.
He knows exactly what he's
he's doing.
I'm going with my gut and I
think that I-I should stick with
him until it gets to a point
where I feel like he'd
turn on me.
>> I know.
>> I'll do whatever it takes to
get to the top, but what I'm
telling you is...
>> Yeah.
>> ...is I want to get
to the top with you.
>> Yeah.
>> We are going to be better of
a pair than you can even
possibly imagine.
>> I agree.
...period.
That's what I really,
really want.
>> And I can swing it.
>> I clearly know that Russell
is running around talking to
everyone and telling everyone
the same thing, but we can
either work with each other or
against each other, and I do
not want to work against him.
Are you kidding?
He's just an incredible force.
>> I do.
>> With Russell, I definitely
feel like I am making a deal
with the devil, but I want the
devil on my side.
>> These are all-stars, but you
know what?
I'm a little above that.
Like Michael Jordan is in
basketball, like Michael Phelps
is in swimming.
There's always somebody that's
above their sport.
And I'm the best player
that ever played this game.
Now guess what?
I get to prove it.
(chuckles)
>> Sweet!
>> All right!
Nice!
>> Man, we got a net.
>> Wow!
We have a net?
>> A net! Oh, sweet.
>> Well, here we are, guys.
>> Here we are.
>> Heroes?
>> We're heroes!
>> Yeah!
>> Heroes!
(laughter)
>> "Return, revenge and
redemption."
>> Well...
>> All right.
>> Shall we take a
celebratory dip?
>> Yes.
>> I think so.
>> It takes a little bit to get
back into the rhythm of
Survivor and go, "All right, I
"remember this.
It's gonna be miserable."
A little chillier than you'd
think, isn't it?
But you just don't remember
what it feels like to be
stranded and know you're just
at the tip, you're at the
beginning of a long journey,
if you're lucky.
>> It's got to be the best
first-day challenge I've ever
seen in any Survivor.
Sugar got topless.
(laughter)
Stephenie dislocated her
shoulder and put it back in,
and Rupert broke one toe in
three places.
>> You know, the challenge, I
think our team showed its
it's strength.
Unfortunately, I didn't.
You know, the challenge was
rough for me.
I don't like losing at
anything, and I got beat by
Coach.
So I'm so rusty on the game,
but I'm having a good time.
>> We're making our first group
decision.
>> Oh, goody!
>> I mean, we can just build
something really quick
right now.
Yeah, we can always move it.
>> Um, the two oldest men...
>> Oh, no, no, no!
>> can we have, can we...?
(laughter)
can we just...?
>> The two older men, could
you guys keep your opinions
to yourself?
>> We're all kids, and we don't
know anything.
So-- what do you guys think?
Is it better to have more bugs
in the jungle or would it be
too cold out here or can we
just build a shelter to block
the wind?
>> I say here.
>> I say front.
All for here?
>> We'll have a fire.
>> We can start a fire
in the rain.
>> All right.
>> Yay!
>> Wow, this is light.
There you go!
Get it, girl!
>> I love my tribe.
We have a good aura.
We have good energy.
You know, we all have a good
work ethic.
If you just wanna help, like,
start putting 'em up, maybe, I
guess, right?
>> Yeah.
>> We know what needs to be
done, and we work together,
and I feel really lucky to be
on the Heroes' side and to have
the team I have.
>> I think we should use the
big ones, maybe, for the top,
higher up, so it could be
more...
Like, everything was going
right.
We have good karma right now.
It's great.
>> You know what we need?
Like, the post to split the
coconut husk on.
You got to get, like, a short,
pointy...
(chicken clucking)
Thought I heard some clucking,
and went around and looked in
the bush, and I see some
movement out of the corner
of my eye, and here comes a
rooster, three hens, walking
right out.
Guys, look at this.
There are at least three
chickens right here.
>> Chicken?
>> Stay right here, Tom.
I'm gonna go around the
other side.
>> Here's another one
right here.
>> Great, we got four chickens.
There's another one.
>> Yep.
>> Well, we got three people
still, so anybody that can catch
a chicken, come this way.
>> Go around the back, guys,
and draw them out towards us.
>> Does he have the net?
>> Yeah, grab that fishing net,
would be great.
>> Bring it up.
Everybody who's free should
just surround them.
Hey, uh...
how about if we have four of us
go, like, one, two, and then
just throw it out like this?
>> So, are you ready?
>> Don't overthrow.
>> Shh, shh, shh.
>> Are we gonna throw it on
three?
>> We're gonna throw it on
three.
>> ...two...
We're just practicing.
>> ...three.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> No, it's getting away!
>> Got it, got it!
>> You got it, man.
(chickens clucking)
(whooping)
>> We got ourselves chicken!
>> Winner, winner, chicken
dinner!
>> Yeah! Winner, winner, chicken
>> I have seen my share of
chickens, and I've caught my
share of 'em, but never in the
wild, and to actually, you know,
catch them successfully, all
four of them, that's
incredible.
>> Oh, my God.
I don't believe it.
>> I know.
>> Oh, my God, you guys!
>> Nice work.
>> They are cute, aren't they?
Watching these guys working
together, I'm ecstatic.
Coming back into Survivor, I
know the first five days are
the hardest time.
I haven't hit that wall yet.
Maybe in our tribe, we won't.
I mean, shoot, we found
chickens?
We're going to be out of the
elements.
It's good to be a Hero.
>> What'd you guys think of
the challenge today?
>> Let's review-- we're glad
that Rupert stubbed his toe.
>> Aargh!
(laughter)
>> The thing is, like, one part
of me, like, wants to have
sympathy for him, but another
side of me, I almost relished
the fact that they got injured.
I was like, "Good for them."
(laughter)
>> I definitely had mixed
emotions about losing the
challenge, because whereas
personally it made a statement,
the tribe lost.
I had him the whole time.
There was not one point in that
challenge where I thought he
was gonna get the better of me.
>> You were very relaxed.
I saw it in your face.
>> Well, there was this sec
that he almost took off running
and you had to tackle him down.
>> Yeah.
>> We were like, "No!"
>> Everybody thought that Colby
was gonna have his way with me.
The tribe was taking about it
long after I'd forgotten it,
about how I'd gone out there
and basically frog-marched Colby
to, uh, to the mat at the end.
So it was very fulfilling.
And at the very end, dude, I
was, like, kind of, like, moved
him, moved him, moved him, mat.
>> Bam.
(laughter)
>> It was... I enjoyed every
second of that.
Coach, what a surprise.
Honestly, I'm-I'm very surprised
by Coach.
There's just something about
him, and I don't know what it
is yet.
I'm definitely gonna make it a
point to get to know Coach.
I know I'm stealing Coach's
mantra here, but I'm going into
this like a warrior.
'Cause that's really what you
have to do.
>> How did you know that was my
mantra?
>> Uh, I heard stuff about you.
>> Yeah, okay.
One thing that appeals to me
about Jerri is that she's a
different kind of girl, and, uh,
that interests me, because I'm
a different kind of guy.
>> Randy, I hear you chuckling
over there.
>> (laughing): No, I'm laughing
at Colby's face.
Actually, he looked a little
scared.
...you don't step away from
love.
If it's hitting you in the
face, you grab ahold to it.
You never know, man.
>> You never know.
>> I would never get in the way
of true love.
>> Go for it, dude. Go for it.
>> I agree.
>> Are you talking about
Parvati?
(laughter)
>> I have never in a million
years would think about coming
out on Survivor and actually
being interested in somebody.
But Jerri and I, we have a
little connection.
>> How's it going, Coach?
I'm keeping my eye on him.
>> Are you guys playing Cupid?
>> Yes.
You and the dragon slayer.
(laughing)
>> Ooh, I see romance blooming
between Jerri and Coach.
And Jerri's in total denial,
but she totally flirts, and
she's, I think, in spite of
herself, a little bit in love
with the dragon slayer.
>> I'm setting you up with
Coach.
What's the problem?
You know what?
Love finds you sometimes, and
you don't even know it.
>> Well, you do know that just
by cuddling together one night,
we created a whole little...
>> I know.
>> ...controversial buzz that
could potentially not be...
I don't know.
>> Well, I just think we carry
on our business.
I mean, I think that if we just
go about our day and we don't
have too many talks like this,
unless we're walking down the
beach that way.
>> I know, right?
>> But it sucks, because, you
know, obviously, I want to talk
to you.
>> I know, I know.
>> The girls were joking about
it.
They were, like, "Oh, the black
widow and the dragon slayer--
what a combination."
Hey, you never know, we might
pair up and run this game.
But we need to be careful,
Jerri and I, of having the
appearance of being in an
unbreakable alliance.
>> Will you promise me if I
should worry about something,
let me know?
>> Well, don't worry about
anything.
Okay?
>> Okay. Yeah, 'cause the
last... I hate feeling alone
out here.
>> Don't... You're not alone.
>> It's the worst feeling in
the world.
>> No, you shouldn't be worried.
You're with the dragon slayer,
man-- don't you worry about
that.
>> We got a good group.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> Here's the thing, this is
between me and you right here,
it's got to be.
But I'm willing to make an
alliance right now with you.
'Cause I haven't made an
alliance with nobody, brother.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't want the physical
threat of being thrown out of
here.
We should never lose, man.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't want flower power to
be running over this thing like
it was, you know.
>> Hey, I went through it, so...
>> I know, man.
>> It was terrible.
>> James and I, you know, we're
buddies right off the bat.
We both work hard.
He's a guy's guy.
I mean, we can talk straight up.
Anything he tells me, I
believe it.
Could I ever beat James if it
was me and him in the final two?
No. But... I don't see me and
him in the final two.
I'd rather see us rock on
through and stay strong, dude.
>> Yeah, let's keep the guys
together.
>> If we go to... That's...
hey, that's the deal.
>> No, for real.
>> I'm gonna form alliances
with everyone I can.
My strategy is to keep everyone
on my side, man.
>> Here's the thing, Candice...
...for J.T. and James.
>> I know that James and Amanda
played together.
>> I don't know them, but I
know that there's people that,
you know...
>> Yeah. That's my concern.
>> The first couple of days are
always the worst out here.
Because you don't have
everything settled, you don't
know everybody, and so it's
always kind of awkward.
>> What do you know about Cirie?
>> You mean, like, how she
played the game?
>> I don't know anything about
her.
>> I don't know her.
>> Yeah.
>> Are they friends?
>> Going into the game again,
I'm worried about people who
have a history together,
they've played on seasons
before together.
And I don't really have anyone
that I have a solid history
with going into the game.
>> Well, didn't take long for
the game to start.
>> (laughs): Yeah.
>> We're back again.
>> I know.
What do you think?
>> I don't know yet.
>> I don't know, I'm trying
to...
>> Trying to assess the
situation.
>> Yeah. (laughs)
Exactly.
We can't be off alone like
this, though.
>> James, myself, and Cirie,
you know, we've played this
game together before.
I've played this twice with
James-- in China and Micronesia.
I've played it once with Cirie,
and Cirie and I went to the end
together.
We were in an alliance the
whole time, so we're going to
have to watch our distance,
because if people think we're
too chummy, it could... it could
definitely play against us.
>> So, how you doing, my friend?
Welcome to Samoa. (laughing)
>> Thank God we're on the same
tribe.
>> It's good to be here with you
again-- yeah, that's great!
It's like déjà vu, right?
So, um, hopefully, we can just
run this thing where we avoid
Tribal Council in the beginning.
>> Yeah, but I'm trying to
think who... who do you want to
get involved with here.
>> Right.
My closest ally is Stephenie.
We played well together in our
season in Palau.
And, uh, I was thrilled to see
her back here on this beach in
my tribe.
I think Colby... Colby, J.T.
and you would be my choice, but
like you said, we don't know
what they're thinking is...
>> That's what I was thinking.
>> I'm gonna try to work with
Stephenie as far as we can, but
she might not be my smartest
end player.
If I were to get that far in
the game and were to face a
jury, I want somebody else who
won the million dollars to sit
next to me.
So, you know, seeing you right
away, I will... you know, you
want to make some kind of an
oath, whatever.
You and I need each other in the
finals, because we both won
the money.
>> They have to choose one of
us.
>> If either one of us, no
matter how good a game we play,
goes up against someone who
didn't win...
>> We lose.
Me and you, man.
>> It's a good plan.
>> People are expecting me to be
that guy they saw on Tocantins,
you know, that guy who stuck by
his word and done everything he
had to do.
But this game is completely
different, because everyone's
already seen me play.
>> You're my guy for the end.
>> All right, you got me.
>> Right.
>> You know, I need you...
and you need me.
>> We need each other.
>> To win this game of Survivor,
you have to have a dark side
somewhere.
You have to be willing to
sacrifice some of your
integrity to make it far in
this game.
And I'm not looking to save
my hero name.
I'm here to do what I have to
do to win this game.
So it's going to be a whole
different ballgame for me.
(sighs)
>> Sandra, do you know how to
do this?
(laughter)
>> This is not working.
I think I'm not going to do
this anymore.
>> We got ten people here.
They don't want to do anything
for more than, like, ten minutes
at a time.
>> I know.
>> But nobody has any energy,
because we don't have any water.
>> Everybody's going to be dead
for this challenge if we don't
get water.
>> Yeah.
>> We have to build a fire.
It's been six years since I've
played the game, and a lot has
changed.
Like, there's nobody here that
wants to do anything.
They don't want to build a
shelter.
They don't want to try to get a
fire going.
It's not that they don't know
what to do-- they've all played
Survivor before.
Sandra's won the game.
So they know what they're
doing.
And it's, like, ripping at my
every fiber. Ugh!
My wife told me, have patience.
Amber, I'm trying.
>> You're-you're just gonna
carve a gouge in there and...
>> A little gouge.
Then I'm going to take another
piece of bamboo and rub it
like this.
>> You know, nobody's going to
get voted out for not making
fire, and nobody's going to get
to stay...
>> If they do.
>> ...trying to make fire.
So why don't we blow it off?
>> Do you think? (laughs)
You're just going to wear
yourself out.
>> You know, I played this game
before, and if you don't have
flint and steel, you can't make
fire.
Not by rubbing two sticks
together.
This game lasts 39 days.
I think we'll get fire by the
end of 39 days.
>> Now, slow, short strokes at
first.
A little faster, guys.
>> Starting to get some smoke.
>> Yeah!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Keep going.
All right, real fast now.
>> Here we go!
(loud grunting)
>> Three, two, one.
Do it.
>> Flames.
>> It's happening.
>> This is happening.
>> Rob, you're the man down
here, too.
None of us are gonna do
anything.
You're in charge.
>> Here we go.
(excited shouts)
>> Oh, yeah!
Unbelievable!
>> I'm still the same guy I was
the first time I played this
game-- that competitiveness,
that cutthroat-ness, that's me.
At the same time, a lot has
happened with me personally in
my life in the six years since
I've played this game last.
You know, I got married, I had
a kid, I'm learning compromise
and patience.
But look at these people, you
know?
Not the brightest bulbs, and
I'm here trying to make the
most of it, trying to make it
work.
>> We got fire!
(excited shouts)
>> Look at it!
>> Wow!
>> Beautiful!
>> Amazing!
>> I wouldn't have believed it
if I didn't see it.
>> (laughs): I know, man.
>> Now, I got to tell you, I'm a
little in awe of Rob, and I'm
not like that with people.
You know, he's played it twice.
He's intuitive and ingenious
and very smart.
So that's great.
I mean, he's a great guy to
have on the tribe.
You are the man.
And it's, like, when you're
talking, I'm just, like...
I'm, like, literally hanging on
every word.
>> I appreciate it, I do.
>> I'm serious.
I'm, like, hanging on every
word.
>> We made fire, and now
Coach is going off with Boston
Rob like he's a hero or
something.
>> I'm bromancing on my idol,
what can I say?
>> Rob, he thinks he's the boss
of the camp.
He thinks he's in control.
But this is my mountain, and I'm
still the king of the hill.
Survivor is my palace.
So I'm still the king, unless
I'm dethroned.
And you know what?
That ain't gonna happen.
>> PROBST: Coming up on this
special two-hour season
premiere of Survivor: Heroes
vs. Villains:
>> We have to divide them.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Heroes!
>> PROBST: Coach leading the
tribe of Villains, using all of
that life experience in a kayak.
>> It's only a matter of time
before that tribe
self-destructs.
>> It's time to cut his throat.
>> Being able to get out in the
ocean, that's where I feel most
comfortable.
But my toe is broken at least
two places.
And I haven't caught a darn
fish yet.
I think it'd be better off
for me right now, especially
with my darn toe, to be a
worker bee.
I'm going to start us a fire.
You can do this.
Just start the damn fire.
(whispers): Gosh darn it.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, you can do this.
>> Rupert the fire maker.
(laughing): He shaved half the
magnesium off the flint, you
know, and still couldn't get the
fire.
You don't want to say anything.
You just sit there and watch,
because his ego is so humongous.
What can you say?
>> Yeah, I'll tell you why I
can't, Rupe.
>> You want to go ahead, but,
uh, I've been sitting here
for a while, and... we've had
some hellacious piles of
magnesium.
God!
It's okay.
It's a state of mind.
Making fire is as much a state
of mind as anything.
(birds chirping)
>> Wow, that's looking...
Now we're talking.
>> Yay.
The only thing that I'm worried
about is my darn broken toe.
If it starts coming up more and
more about how much pain I'm
really in and what I really can
bring to this tribe-- because I
haven't done a whole lot yet--
that worries me.
Wow. Good for you guys.
♪ ♪
>> You just scoot up.
Tyson and I decided we wanted
to try to climb this coconut
tree to get the palm fronds off.
Think it's a little too
dangerous?
>> It's pretty precarious...
with the wind.
>> The wind is blowing up there
now.
>> Get down.
>> She's, like, "Why'd you
let him do that?"
If he breaks his leg.
>> He's a father.
>> Yeah, I was told not to do
anything stupid.
You go ahead and try.
I could probably get up there
and get them, but why would I
risk falling and getting hurt?
Man, it's higher than it looks.
But I know somebody that, you
know, is so full of themself,
when you give them a challenge,
they're just going to have to
do it because they're the
greatest and the best, and
you know, every day out here
they get stronger.
>> He wants to be a Hero, but
he's really a Villain, so we'll
see how this goes.
>> I say don't do it.
>> Get your ass up that tree,
will ya?
>> Boston Rob and I do have a
good time together, you know?
I like talking to him, because
he's really-- he's sharp, and I
like that, and he's gonna
challenge me, and I think I'm
gonna challenge him.
I think I need somebody that's
able to sharpen me, as iron
sharpens iron.
>> Come on, you can do it.
>> Oh, at least he'll land in
the water.
>> You want to make a bet?
>> What?
>> If he makes it or not?
I'll bet you a dollar.
>> The person that I think I'm
most like is Boston Rob.
Seeing Rob here, it reminds me
of when he played the first
time-- I loved him.
Okay.
>> All right?
>> All right, a dollar.
A dollar that he won't make it
to the top, and you're saying
a dollar that he'll do it?
>> He's going to do it.
>> That's someone I could see
myself aligning with until it's
time to cut his throat.
>> I bet on you!
>> What?
>> I bet that you would make it.
>> I bet that you'd fall in the
water.
>> Oh, he's giving up!
Oh, no, he's giving up!
>> You're not a warrior!
Get up there!
>> Get back down, get back down.
>> Man!
>> Right to Sandra, winner,
from... from Boston Bob the
loser.
>> Boston Bob.
>> So I bowed out, swallowed my
pride.
It's not worth it.
Tucked my tail, went back down.
>> Man, you cost me.
>> I won.
>> I made a bet and I lost.
>> I could have probably made
it up to that where it starts
getting steep.
>> Coulda, shoulda, woulda,
didn't.
>> But it's not worth it.
Could I make it up there? Yes.
But if I fall off, I mean, why
risk that?
>> From the Hero to the zero.
>> From the Hero to the zero?
>> Yep.
>> He was a Hero...
>> From the Villain to the never
was.
♪ ♪
>> This game, it's a reflection
of your life, and you don't even
realize it.
I guess in life I always need a
protector of some sort, and
especially in the game of
Survivor.
So now I'm starting to realize
that I've got these sexy young
men on my tribe.
What's going on over there,
Colby?
>> It was night two.
People are starting to fade off
and get some much-needed rest.
That's what we have to have to
stay strong and compete.
>> Is that a satellite or a
shooting star?
>> And Sugar, she just starts
chatting up again, and not
whispering but chatting up loud.
>> You guys are all spooning.
I don't want to spoon, I want
to... (laughs)
>> And then you could start to
feel and see everyone kind of
wrestle awake.
I couldn't even roll over
without her rolling over and
putting her arms around me, or
then when I would just lay
there still like I was in a
coffin, she'd grab my hands and
put them on her.
I'm being flirted with, and I'm
just not interested.
>> Should we go back to
that corner?
Let's go.
Go in the corner where we were.
>> She chased me all around the
shelter.
Wherever I'd go, two seconds
later, she'd show up there.
She's becoming a bit annoying.
Nobody really had a good
night's sleep because of her.
If you ruffle the feathers of
the tribe... (whistles) they'll
get rid of you in a hurry.
>> Has everybody talked about
what they want to eat tonight?
We gotta have boiled eggs,
don't you think?
>> Chicken.
>> You want a chicken?
>> First challenge?
>> No, heck, yeah.
>> And he's the biggest, too,
so...
>> Yep.
>> We're thinking of maybe
cooking a rooster, depending on
how much fish we get.
>> There are some parallels in
how you decide which chicken to
eat in the same way you devour
your enemies in the game of
Survivor.
If they're producing eggs,
they'll probably stay around
camp for a long time.
If they're not, they're going
to start hitting the barbecue.
>> Anybody want to do the honor
or do you want me to go ahead?
>> You do it.
>> Go ahead.
(indistinct chatter, laughing)
>> Oh.
>> Yeah, J.T., he did it
old school.
>> Oh, my God!
>> He just grabbed it by its
neck and spun it around until
it was done.
>> Wow, you are so country.
>> My great-great grandmother
did that to me one time when I
was three and scared the life
out of me.
She took one and grabbed it by
its neck and spun it around and
and popped its head off and
then it run around.
It was traumatic-- like, we were
screaming.
We didn't know what to do.
And I don't know, it was a good
time.
Kind of... kind of very...
it was traumatic.
But it was... it's funny now.
It smells good.
I can smell it already.
>> Mmm!
>> It's pretty good.
>> It is good. Yeah.
>> You know, it's little
victories like the chicken that
get you fired up.
It just goes to show we have
sustainability out here.
That's a huge thing.
>> Thank you.
>> Thanks for cooking, boys.
>> I think the Villains can
stay positive for a short time.
But without fire, without the
small victories, it's only a
matter of time before that
tribe self-destructs.
>> We're living large on Hero
Beach, James.
It's good to be a Hero.
>> Treemail!
>> "This challenge is a big one.
It's not for the stupid or weak.
You've been here before, so
save your excuses at Tribal
Council.
Feel free to speak.
Life's tough enough on the
island, with suffering hunger
and thirst, so don't add to the
humiliation by being the one
who is voted off first."
Ooh...
>> The Villains were beaten the
other day but not broken.
Today, we build ourselves up
again to go out there and to
thrash the Heroes unmercifully.
>> Today is the difference
maker in the whole game.
We gotta win.
>> Hopefully, we will not only
defeat them, but we will beat
them as well, mentally, and...
turn things around for the
better.
>> Villains!
>> Get your evil on!
>> I got my evil right here.
>> Yeah.
>> JEFF PROBST: Come on in,
guys!
So, Heroes, you guys had fire.
J.T., how's it going?
Were you able to get fire going?
>> Yeah, it's been pretty good,
actually.
We're staying a lot drier than
I expected.
>> Our roof is pretty thatched
pretty well so we kept dry.
>> PROBST: Tom, how's the food?
>> Food's going pretty good.
We got lucky with a couple of--
one rooster, three hens, had a
nice breakfast today.
>> PROBST: Rob, what's going on
over at the Villains' camp?
>> Yeah, it's not quite as good
as the way they're talking over
there.
Our shelter is terrible.
>> Well, it's not that bad.
>> It's terrible.
It's terrible.
>> It's bad.
It's really bad.
>> PROBST: And therein lies the
difference between Coach, who
can endure anything, and the
rest of us who would like
something to lie down on.
All right, you guys ready to
get to your first immunity
challenge?
>> Do it.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, for
today's challenge, six tribe
members will race to assemble a
boat.
You must then use seven planks
to keep the boat together.
You'll paddle out, grab a
torch, paddle back, where you
will remove the seven planks
and bring them back to the
start.
The four remaining tribe
members must then solve a
puzzle.
Once you have the puzzle
completed, you will use those
planks to build a ladder to
allow you to place the puzzle
in its appropriate spot.
It's then a race to the top.
First tribe to get all their
members to the top, light their
fire barrel, wins immunity.
This is what you want in this
game.
If you have immunity, you are
safe.
You can't be voted out.
Without it, you are vulnerable.
Losing tribe goes to Tribal
Council where somebody will be
the first person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs.
Villains.
One item of note-- both Candice
and Parvati have both competed
in this challenge in their
original season.
In the Cook Islands they were
on the same tribe.
They were winners.
Today they are opponents.
See how it plays out.
I'll give you a minute to
strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
At stake, immunity, and for the
Villains, fire if they win.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Heroes!
>> Come on, Villains.
Get ugly!
>> PROBST: You need all the
pieces.
You need the planks.
You need your paddles.
You need all of it.
Both tribes doing a good job of
getting all their pieces out in
the water to start putting this
boat together.
James carrying two by himself.
>> That goes here...
>> Hold that.
>> Let's go, guys.
Hey, let's go.
We've got to put these together.
>> Let's go, Heroes!
>> Great job, guys.
>> PROBST: Heroes getting it
together quickly.
Villains already falling behind.
>> One small hole.
>> That one there?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Got to get those
planks in.
That's what's keeping your boat
together.
>> That doesn't fit.
>> PROBST: Parvati, Coach,
Tyson, Courtney, Russell and
Danielle struggling early.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Everything strapped.
>> PROBST: Heroes have their
boat together and they're
heading out.
>> Yeah, Heroes!
>> Keep it up!
>> PROBST: Heroes with a nice
lead right off the bat.
>> You guys, put it together.
Put it together.
>> PROBST: Heroes doing a good
job.
Everybody working together.
>> I need three holes close
together over here.
>> Three holes close together,
could be four-- no...
>> PROBST: Villains starting to
panic a little seeing that lead
increase.
>> They're not even off the
beach.
Now, let's just cruise up on it.
>> PROBST: Heroes are already
at their fire.
J.T. has the torch.
Heroes are now heading back.
Villains finally have their
boat together.
They're heading out.
Heroes look like they've been
paddling together forever.
Great rhythm.
Everybody working together well.
>> Good lead, guys!
Yeah!
>> I hate them so bad.
>> PROBST: Coach leading the
tribe of Villains using all of
that life experience in a kayak.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Villains have their
torch.
Parvati lights it.
Villains are now heading back.
>> Only on the right.
And stroke, stroke.
>> Let's go, come on, guys!
>> Come on, guys.
>> Pull it, pull it, pull it!
>> Run it in!
Run it in!
>> PROBST: You now have to take
that boat apart.
You need those seven planks.
>> Let's go get those planks
off!
You're doing great.
>> PROBST: Once you can get
those planks off, take them and
get up there.
Heroes have their planks.
They're heading up to the
puzzle.
>> Good job, guys!
>> Good job!
>> PROBST: Got to get your
planks here before you can
start on your puzzle.
Heroes now with an early lead.
Working on this puzzle.
Villains, you need to pick it
up.
>> Stroke!
Stroke!
>> Take your time.
Don't panic.
>> PROBST: This is a four-layer
puzzle.
In our 20th season of
Survivor, you can expect
difficult challenges and
difficult puzzles.
>> Get out, get out.
>> PROBST: Villains are back.
Get those seven planks and get
back here.
>> Come on, guys.
>> Wait, wait, that's not right.
>> Got it.
>> PROBST: Villains heading
back with their seven planks.
>> Come on, come on, come on!
>> PROBST: Start!
Villains now working on their
puzzle.
Villains hoping to make up some
time.
Rob, Sandra, Randy, Jerri
working on the puzzle for the
Villains.
>> Wait, there it is.
That's it, that's it.
>> PROBST: It's Amanda, Cirie,
Sugar, and Rupert working for
the Heroes.
The question is, did you pick
the right four to put the
puzzle together?
>> Something has to go down
here.
>> This is here.
>> Come on, guys. You got it.
>> PROBST: Rob and Sandra doing
a great job on the puzzle.
>> I don't think this goes here.
Something's not right.
Something has to go here, you
guys.
>> PROBST: As Amanda and Cirie
start to panic.
Rupert now getting in it for
the Heroes, trying to get
something going.
Heroes had a big lead and it is
all but gone.
Sandra and Rob working
together very well.
>> You guys are doing a good
job.
Come on, guys, you got it.
>> That goes there.
>> PROBST: Sandra feeling very
confident.
Heroes not confident at all.
Sugar watching it fall apart.
And the Heroes are back to the
start.
All the pieces out, they are
starting over.
Villains are now in the lead in
this challenge.
Only five pieces left.
Are they right?
Heroes still trying to figure
out the first piece of this
puzzle.
>> Maybe there are two
different pieces that fit into
the same thing.
Sugar now getting involved.
Villains getting very close.
Do they have it?
They do!
Villains have their puzzle
completed.
Villains have their puzzle put
together.
Now they have to put the seven
planks in the right spot to
build a ladder.
Heroes, you need to keep it
going.
>> This stuff goes underneath
it.
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait,
wait, wait.
>> PROBST: Villains with a big
come-from-behind.
Villains have their ladder
built.
Got to put the puzzle in.
>> Watch your hands.
>> PROBST: It's in.
Everybody to the top.
>> Go, go, go!
>> PROBST: It started as
blowout for the Heroes.
It is ending as a blowout for
the Villains.
>> Light it up, light it up,
light it up!
>> PROBST: Villains win first
immunity challenge!
>> Yeah, baby!
Good job, good job!
>> Man!
>> PROBST: Villains,
congratulations.
Immunity keeps you safe from
Tribal Council.
Fire will hopefully get your
camp in order.
>> Yes!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Sugar, three days
into this game, right on cue,
you're crying.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, Heroes.
Tribal Council tonight.
One of the ten of you will be
the first person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs.
Villains.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Villains, congratulations.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
>> Thank you.
>> If Sugar's having some sort
of emotional breakdown on day
three, she's not fit to be out
here another 36 days.
Losing her, we're going to
miss...
Yeah, I don't think we're going
to miss much.
>> Yeah, how do you like us now,
huh?
>> Yeah!
>> All right!
>> Good job.
>> Good work.
>> Now, we have a relaxing
afternoon.
Nobody has to go cut anybody's
throat.
We just have a nice nice, huh?
>> It was exciting to win the
immunity challenge.
We had to do it because we
didn't want one of our people
to be the first to leave
Heroes vs. Villains.
Now we're trying to figure out
who they're going to send home
and why.
>> Well, Tom and Stephenie are
together.
They were together from before.
James has to be with Cirie and
Amanda and what's the other one?
When push comes to shove and
nobody wants to go home first,
it's about who all you've been
with and who you know.
>> Yeah.
>> What I like about it is they
all shook up now.
Now they are divided.
We have to divide them.
The Heroes got their asses
handed to them.
And, you know what, we were
having a good time just sitting
back loving it.
Oh, I'm happy!
>> Keep going, keep going.
>> It strengthens our tribe and
it weakens the Heroes' tribe.
>> We looked like a team a
little bit today.
Like eight out of ten, 80%...
>> A solid B-plus.
>> They got to stab somebody
in the back.
They're over there being
villains.
That's what they're doing.
>> This is not good.
Nobody in a million years would
have guessed we are going to
Tribal Council on day three.
Hopefully, this loss does
nothing to our momentum other
than show us that we're
vulnerable.
They might be a little more
sneaky and a little more game
playey and a little more damn
puzzle oriented, and that's
fine.
>> Well, they wanted it pretty
bad.
>> They needed it.
>> Yeah.
>> And we were a little cocky.
We walked in there like the
heroes.
You know, there's big "S's" on
all of our chests.
This Heroes vs. Villains is
going to be a tough one.
When we thought we had it in
the bag, they showed us we
don't.
>> You guys want some coconuts?
>> Neither was I.
>> What do you think?
>> Amanda?
>> Okay.
>> Okay, we all...?
Well, that's fine with me.
As long as it's not me.
>> It's freaking awesome with
me. Please.
>> Okay.
>> When we lost, I felt really,
really awful.
I helped us lose, I guess,
because I was on the puzzle,
and I felt bad because we had
such a good lead before.
I just was disappointed in
myself.
And scared.
I don't want to talk to anyone.
>> Me, either.
>> I'm so depressed right now.
(laughing)
These are all people, some of
them have all played together
before, and they're really good.
And I think that Amanda and
James are together, so we have
to break that up, if at all
possible.
>> This isn't a bad thing.
>> No.
>> I think Sugar.
I think everyone's thinking
Sugar.
>> Yeah.
>> Is that done?
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> What are you thinking?
>> I'm thinking that you have a
follower and you got one of
the smartest strategic players
in the game.
Why are we taking out the
follower instead of the
strategic player?
Cirie...
>> Oh, Cirie?
>> ...has run this game a few
times. So...
I really believe that when you
identify a threat, you take them
out as soon as possible.
You don't wait.
People did that on my season,
and they waited too long, and
then they didn't get the
opportunity to get rid of me.
So I don't want to have those
regrets that those people had.
>> I have no problem.
>> Just a thought.
Just a thought.
>> I'm down with that.
>> Cirie is just a brilliant
strategist in the game.
She's proven that, so I'm just
a little nervous to give her a
bye tonight.
>> So I told you three my
concerns about Cirie.
>> Cirie-- I worry about her the
most.
>> Right.
>> Cirie's tricky.
>> So, who are we voting for?
That's what I'm...
>> I like Sugar...
>> They're voting for Sugar?
>> Who's voting for Sugar?
>> The other group.
>> Do we need to break up Tom
and Stephenie?
>> I agree.
Because why waste a vote?
And you're not going to be able
to get him later.
So, what are we doing? Tom?
>> Tom or Stephenie.
I'm good with either one.
>> You got to make a decision
which one before we go back,
'cause we're not going to be
able to talk again.
>> Word on the street is, Sugar
is supposed to go tonight.
Why Sugar?
Sugar, yes, she's annoying,
which is even a better reason
for me to keep her around,
because as long as there's
somebody annoying and
somebody... less strong than I
am, then that takes the target
off of me.
So if we could get one of the
stronger players out, like Tom
or Stephenie, that would be
better for me.
So I'd rather not have Sugar go
tonight.
My concern is, if we don't
knock one of them out, like
Stephenie, who ca...
We're going to lose challenges
without Stephenie?
>> Maybe.
She's a really strong swimmer.
>> And can't-- and Sugar is not?
>> I don't think so.
>> I don't know.
I'm just... you know...
>> There is an advantage of
keeping Stephenie right now and
getting rid of Sugar,
physically, like, for the
challenges.
But strategically, Stephenie
has got game and she has to go.
You think Stephenie?
>> The smartest... the smartest
move right now would be
Stephenie.
I mean, think about it.
We want to make moves that's
gonna guarantee us, you know,
getting further in this game.
>> It's so hard, because you
want to keep your team strong,
but strategically, you have to
put yourself in a good position.
Either you're doing it for
challenges, or you're going to
get rid of someone for
strategic reasons.
Or you just don't like them.
Cirie and I are here for blood,
okay?
We are here to win this thing.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Behind each of you is
a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach a flame, dip it in,
and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council, because in this
game, as you know, fire
represents your life.
As long as you have fire,
you're still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
That will be the case for one
of you tonight.
First, let me just welcome you
to Tribal.
We're 40 feet in the air in the
middle of the jungle, no roof.
If it rains, we will get wet.
As I'm sure will happen once or
twice out here.
I just want to look at some of
the reasons you might vote
somebody off.
Tom, how big a factor do you
think prior relationships-- you
and Stephenie, Amanda and
Cirie, people that have played
together before that others
might look at and think: they've
got to be friends, they got to
be in an alliance, they know
each other?
>> I think that we all worried
about that coming into it.
I think it's kind of been
pushed to the side now.
We realize that you just got
to give everybody a clean slate
and take it from there.
So, I'm not too worried about
the previous relationships.
>> PROBST: Sugar, you haven't
played with anybody.
Do you buy what Tom's saying?
Is it fine, it's a clean slate?
"I don't really care if they
knew somebody else before."
>> Well, I thought that was a
really good speech, but I do
think that that is definitely a
factor-- people who have played
together and people who knew
each other and people who hang
out, or whatever.
>> PROBST: What about past
success?
Amanda, you've played twice,
and you've made it to the end
both times.
Do you find yourself already
trying to deflect some of the
attention that might be on you?
>> You know, one thing that I
did do in both my seasons to
get to the end was make loyal
alliances.
So I think in a way it's a
positive thing for me.
And, yeah, I haven't won.
Like, obviously, we all know,
I'm not good at Tribal Council.
>> Yeah, that was the best
Tribal Council question you've
ever answered.
>> See? I'm working on it.
>> You answered that really
correctly.
I'm surprised.
I'd say it out loud.
>> Shut up, James.
>> That was the best.
>> PROBST: You're surprised and
I'm excited.
>> Obviously.
>> It took me a while, but I'm
getting the hang of it.
So, yeah, it's both.
I mean, there's people in this
game that have won.
I mean, come on, you know.
>> PROBST: Cirie, you're the
woman that stayed at home and
watched Survivor on the couch.
And now here you are for the
third time-- yet another reason
to get rid of somebody.
She's grown into a bona fide
threat to win the game.
How do you defend that, first
Tribal Council?
>> Well, like you said, Jeff,
everybody here is a threat.
If they weren't threatening,
they wouldn't be here.
>> PROBST: Steph, that's really
what we're getting at, at this
first Tribal Council.
Is there's a reason to get rid
of every single person up here.
>> Well, I think, as far as
trying to make a decision
tonight, it's the first one,
and that's the hardest, I think.
But we don't want to come back
here.
I mean, what I'm doing is I'm
going to go with who I think is
the weakest for the team right
now.
And will help us stay the
strongest we can to continue to
win.
>> PROBST: Let's talk about
today's challenge.
James, first half of the
challenge, you guys smoked them
by a long ways.
Then we got to the puzzle.
Amanda, Sugar, Cirie, Rupert--
disaster.
>> It's sucked because nobody
was focusing.
Everybody had their own opinion.
It was like everybody wanted to
solve the puzzle differently.
But hopefully, they'll focus
next time because this just
can't happen no more.
>> PROBST: Cirie, if it's you
tonight, is it fair to take it
because you were one of the
people that blew it on the
puzzle?
>> I don't think one challenge
should determine your worth in
the long run of this game.
It could have been Tom and
Stephenie, and they could have
lost the puzzle.
>> PROBST: Sugar, you were one
of the four people that blew it
on the puzzle.
>> I know.
>> PROBST: There's no debate
about that.
Would it be fair to say "Voting
Sugar out"?
>> Well, that's why I was
crying.
>> PROBST: Because you're
afraid that might be the reason?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Would that be
criteria enough for you to get
rid of somebody?
>> No, not me.
I wouldn't vote somebody out
just because they were part of
a team that didn't win the
challenge.
>> PROBST: Candice, you got to
vote somebody out.
Does it make it easier for you
to say "Well, I could just
simply blame it on the puzzle"?
>> I think the people who
stepped up to do the puzzle
were pretty brave, so I think
we should appreciate that they
stepped up to do that and not
start voting people out for
that because otherwise nobody
is ever going to do a puzzle.
>> PROBST: Tom, do you vote
tonight based on long-term game
or short-term game?
>> I think that people are
developing their relationships,
and kind of everyone is always
looking towards the endgame,
but that's not what we're
working on now.
We're working on staying strong
with your best people, and
let's not come back here
anymore and we don't have to
worry about who we're voting
out.
>> PROBST: Candice, a lot of
these people know each other.
Is the first Tribal Council
maybe an opportunity to take
one person out of the equation
and really change things up?
>> I think the first Tribal
Council is an opportunity to do
anything.
We've got ten people here, and
there's a lot of different
ideas going around.
So, yes...
Or no.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: All right, well,
clearly there's a legitimate
reason to vote every single
person out.
The only thing left to do is
find out who that person is
going to be.
It is time to vote.
Candice, you're up.
♪ ♪
(thunder rumbling)
>> PROBST: I'll go tally
the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Sugar.
Sugar.
Two votes Sugar.
That's three votes Sugar.
Sugar.
That's four votes Sugar.
Amanda.
Four votes Sugar, one vote
That's five votes Sugar, one
vote Amanda.
First person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs.
Villains-- Sugar.
>> Okay.
One of you all better win.
>> PROBST: Sugar, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: All right, first
person voted out of this game,
a Hero.
After you get back to camp and
get your fire going, should be
one thing on your mind--
getting even.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Try to stay dry.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for
scenes from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> Rob?
Rob.
Uh-oh.
>> Can open your eyes for us?
>> PROBST: Rob, can you hear me?
>> It's not a great feeling to
be the first person voted off.
I was crying today because I'm
dramatic and I felt like I lost
the game for everybody.
And I think they did probably
make the right decision in
voting me out because I am I'd
say the weakest link, although
I give it my all.
But I can't wait to get some
clothes on.