>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
With their numbers dwindling,
each of the Villains were
making plans for a possible
merge.
>> If we merge, I have control
of the Villain camp, complete
control.
>> PROBST: Russell thought he
was pulling all the strings, but
Parvati made moves of her own.
>> Another immunity idol is
hidden at your camp.
>> PROBST: She tracked down a
hidden immunity idol, telling
only her friend Danielle.
>> Right now, Russell doesn't
need to know.
>> PROBST: While the outcasts,
Courtney and Sandra, merely
wanted to survive.
>> It's inevitable that me or
Courtney are going home.
>> PROBST: The Heroes were
equally sure a merge was coming,
and even more sure that Russell
was on the outs with the
Villains.
>> That women's alliance looks
very strong.
>> PROBST: So they came up with
a plan to pull in Russell by
giving him an idol with
instructions to take out
Parvati.
>> This is your chance to show
you're not a Villain.
>> PROBST: At the last immunity
challenge...
>> Done.
>> PROBST: Heroes win immunity!
...the Heroes celebrated another
win as J.T. gave Russell an idol
and a chance to become a hero.
(thunder rumbling)
But Russell's a Villain.
>> You don't hand the enemy the
idol.
>> PROBST: In a brilliant
double-cross, Russell kept both
the idol and his ally,
Parvati...
>> Shut up!
>> PROBST: ...as he and his
female accomplices laughed all
the way to Tribal Council, where
they voted out Courtney.
Courtney, the tribe has spoken.
And Sandra was left all alone,
angry at her own tribe.
We are now even-- five Villains,
five Heroes.
With both tribes equal in
number, the real battle is
about to begin.
Who will be voted out tonight
in Heroes vs. Villains?
>> Day 25.
Man!
>> We need a change.
>> I just want to see Russell
and four girls.
>> Oh.
We seriously better merge today.
>> I mean, it's just, like, "Oh,
day 25."
Something's got to happen, you
know.
Please, give us a merge.
Give us a challenge.
Give us anything.
>> This is exponentially worse
than I ever remember it.
>> I hope we get treemail.
That's all we can do.
>> Us five, the family, have
been together a pretty long
time now.
It's taking its toll on us.
>> I hope I'm not pissing
anybody off too much.
>> I think we all are.
>> I try and keep quiet...
>> I'm pretty sure I'm annoying
someone.
>> Oh. Oh, my gosh!
>> What is this?
>> "Heroes..."
>> BOTH: "...do not open this
box until you have the key."
>> "Make room in your camp."
>> BOTH: "Company will be
arriving soon."
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> They're bringing the key.
"Company will be arriving soon."
>> I wonder what that key is to.
>> I know.
>> Oh, I hope it's a treasure.
I do love treasure.
>> A hidden treasure.
>> Oh, we've got something...
>> You guys, it's an Hawaiian
sling...
>> That's a real one.
>> ...with a key on it.
>> With a key.
>> And a note.
>> A key?
>> What is it the key to?
>> All right.
(overlapping chatter)
>> A map!
>> It's a map to the Heroes'
camp.
>> Get the hell out of here.
Let me see.
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Do we know...?
>> We are merging!
>> Do we know how to...? Okay.
>> We just got treemail, and
it comes with a map to our new
home.
If it is a merge, it's okay with
me, 'cause it's right up my
alley.
We're going over to the Heroes
home turf and weeding them out
one at a time.
We know for a fact that I have
to go to J.T., explain to him
why Parvati's not gone.
>> We are going to go to J.T.
and tell him you used his
idol...
>> Be, like, "Than you."
>> ...to save yourself last
night.
"Thank you." You're going to
play that.
>> He's going to say, "Why
didn't you vote Parvati out?"
What I want to do is say that we
both played an idol at the same
time.
>> Because I thought the girls
were revolting.
>> No.
>> So then when the next time we
go to Tribal, you're going to
tell them that you're voting
with them.
>> Right.
>> And they want Parvati off
first.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah?
>> So then you're going to use
the idol to save yourself, and
then, who's going to go home,
one of them?
>> Yeah, J.T. will go home.
>> Shh. Shh. Quiet.
>> With all the other Heroes, we
do.
>> You know, Sandra's walking
around.
Just be quiet.
>> I know!
>> So be quiet.
>> Right now, I do think I have
the only hidden immunity idol
in pocket.
The people that know about it
are the people that have to
know about it-- my whole tribe,
except for Sandra.
We're not going to tell her
anything.
That idol is going to help the
Villain tribe weed out one of
their members on the Heroes'
tribe.
I'm going have them eating out
of my hands.
>> Five of us, five of them.
They're going down in flames.
>> Are we ready for war?
>> Villain flames.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> The Heroes are just going to
have to watch out, 'cause the
Villains are coming.
Right now, Russell and I have
both of the hidden immunity
idols that are in this game,
which puts us in the king and
queen position.
>> Here they are.
Here they are.
>> Huh?
>> Here they come.
>> Well, the queen has to keep
some secrets, so I would like to
keep my hidden immunity idol
a secret.
Only my lady in waiting,
Danielle, knows about it, and
the king will not know about my
hidden immunity idol until the
time is right.
>> This ought to be interesting.
>> Oh, yes.
>> We need help!
>> Heavy!
>> First thing I noticed when I
looked down the beach and saw
the Villains coming was Parvati.
Then, you know, I saw Russell's
legs behind the Sears box, and
I was, like, "Oh, thank God."
>> How are you?
>> I got it.
(overlapping chatter)
>> Oh, my God.
>> My back.
>> So I figured Russell played
the idol.
Parvati had to have played an
idol.
Therefore, there's no idols in
the game.
Parvati's got to be the first
to go.
It's a known fact.
>> Good to see you, brother.
>> Brother.
>> What's up, Russ?
Welcome aboard, my friend.
>> Hey, let's see what we got
in the box.
(overlapping chatter)
>> Yeah.
(whooping and cheering)
>> Oh, fudge.
>> "Heroes and Villains, replace
your old buffs with the new
ones."
>> Yay!
(cheering)
>> "You must come with a new
tribe name, design a new tribe
flag and begin the next phase
of your journey."
>> They're like half a feet.
(whooping and cheering)
(overlapping chatter)
>> Hey there's ham.
>> Be careful with the eggs
here.
>> Oh!
>> It's a big ham.
(Jerri whoops)
>> It's a party!
>> Yum.
>> Oh, my God, that's so good.
>> When the box got sprung open,
you know, the vegetables and
fruit are flying, you still in
the back of your mind think,
"We're still two tribes," but
when the black buffs came out,
that tells you real quick, old
tribes are done.
This is a whole new ball game.
>> Winners.
>> The what?
>> We're all winners.
We're all all-stars.
We're all something good and
positive.
Why do you have to keep the
Villain attitude?
But I guess that's what Villains
do.
(overlapping chatter)
>> It's in the... it's in the...
>> Really?
>> Oh, you're not far from me
at all.
>> No deal. I live in...
>> Do you know I learned to weld
last year?
>> Really?
>> I MIG weld, yeah.
>> No way.
>> I built a covered wagon from
scratch.
>> Conestoga wagon. No way.
>> Yup.
>> He had a parasite in his
butt.
You can see it.
It's like a worm in his skin.
>> If I had that, I think I'd
cut myself.
Had to take it out.
>> And it moves, and he can't
get rid of it.
>> Bamboo burns too quick.
>> It's hot. It's hot.
>> You all right?
>> Fine.
>> Parvati?
>> What?
Nothing.
Leave me alone!
No, I don't want to talk.
None of the Heroes are happy
that I'm here.
They wanted to get rid of me
before, and they're probably
all be shocked that I'm still
here.
I definitely don't feel like
I'm part of this tribe, so I'm
thinking they're going to vote
for me because they want me
gone.
Like, do these people think I'm
stupid?
>> Yeah.
>> Do they think I'm stupid?
Like, Amanda's played with me
before.
>> They think they have the
game right now, and let them
think that.
Just play... play it like...
>> That's what... That's what I
am. I'm, like...
>> Play right into it.
>> That's what I was doing, and
now it's just, like, I'm over
it.
I'm offended by how these Heroes
are treating me.
They don't know it yet, but
they're about to be picked off
one by one.
Don't talk to me.
It'll get you in trouble.
>> No, I won't.
>> You know, this is the first
time I've been comfortable since
day four.
>> I imagine so.
>> The hidden immunity idol?
>> When did she use it?
>> We both stood up and looked
at each other.
>> Oh, man.
(laughter)
Oh, man.
>> So everybody but Courtney.
And Courtney voted for Jerri.
Everybody else voted for
Courtney.
This is where I stand.
This is it for me.
So don't even have any doubt.
>> I don't doubt you.
I don't doubt you.
>> Don't have any...
Don't even worry.
>> Just let this happen.
>> That's right.
>> Just breathe.
>> Breathe.
>> That's exactly right.
>> Yeah.
>> Giving Russell the hidden
immunity idol could blow up in
my face.
I mean, he could have never been
going home.
You know, he could be the leader
of the girls over there.
Do I believe it?
Not a chance in the world.
So I mean, I trust him
explicitly.
>> Exactly right.
>> Hook, line, and sinker.
They're biting everything I tell
them.
This is going to be way easier
than I thought.
>> You're darn right.
>> That's right.
>> That's good.
It's going to be a wonderful
thing.
>> You know how some people
forgive but don't forget?
Well, I don't forgive and I
don't forget.
The Heroes don't know that
Russell is the kingpin and that
Parvati's his right-hand man.
Russell's trying to play up this
thing like all these women are
about to get rid of him.
I hope I get my revenge 'cause
it's going to be good.
>> So what happened last night?
>> Courtney's the last person
from my alliance.
They didn't want me and Courtney
over here together.
That's why Courtney had to go.
I'm the last one standing and I
have to be babysat, and if they
catch me talking, I'm gone next.
You guys are done, starting with
the men.
You better-- I got to-- I got to
keep you on the low-low.
I'll tell you on the low-low.
>> Right.
Okay.
>> But whatever Russell says,
agree to it, but he's lying if
he says that the women are
running the show.
>> Got you.
Sandra just gave me some really
good information.
Russell told us that Parvati
used her immunity idol last
night.
That is not true.
I don't know if we're getting
played or not, but Russell might
be running the show, and if
Sandra is true-- and I have to
believe Sandra-- Russell is
playing us.
Boy.
This is where the game gets
crazy.
>> All right, now scramble that
joker up or them eggs are
gonna be brown on the bottom.
>> Do you guys want your egg
boiled or scrambled?
>> Oh, I don't care.
>> Um, whatever you guys do.
>> Okay. Just asked
if you cared.
>> Whatever you have.
Whatever you're inspired to
make, I'll eat it.
>> Okay. (both chuckle)
>> The egg is really good.
>> That is a damn good
breakfast.
>> Yup.
>> I'm gonna find a banana.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Oh, my God, it's like
all I need.
You're not hungry?
>> Y'all still got breakfast on
me, don't ya?
>> We just ate.
>> Why do they want to
eat again?
They can't be eating all
their food.
>> Look at this one. (chuckles)
>> They're the greedy-ass,
eating-ass, pain-in-the-ass
tribe.
In our Hero tribe, coconuts are
aplenty.
Anyone can open any coconuts
they want.
With the other food: the bananas
the papayas, we divide that up
a hundred-percent even.
I cannot wait to start voting
some of these Villains out of
our camp.
>> That's more than I eat
in three days.
>> I'm already tired of 'em.
>> Not very good.
>> And they've only been here
two days.
>> This one might be.
It's rotten.
>> Alls I'm saying you got
to watch 'em.
You got to watch all of them.
If Russell is playing us...
>> He's not.
>> Now listen to me.
Don't be so quick.
Let me just tell you the
scenario, okay?
If Russell didn't use that damn
immunity idol, and he's got all
of us voting for Parvati, those
four can put one of us out.
>> But I'm telling you Parvati
wouldn't be in this game if she
didn't play her idol.
No question. I asked.
I believe that.
>> I don't think so either.
>> You have faith in Russell.
Don't trust him.
He's on the Villain side
for a reason!
J.T. believes wholeheartedly
that Russell is on our side
and indebted to us now.
I don't.
So we might just plan on
changing our five votes just
before we go in there;
whoever Russell says.
>> Yep.
>> We don't put that person, but
we look right at him and say,
"Okay. Stay the course."
>> Yeah, we will do whatever it
takes, the first vote.
>> We're together to the end,
brother, to the end.
>> We're good.
> All right, this is,
this is...
>> Rupert is really skeptical of
Russell, so just to make sure
Rupert's okay, the Heroes are
gonna tell Russell we're voting
for someone, and then the five
of us are gonna vote for
someone else.
So it's good just to test.
We don't want to make a dumb
decision, and then be, you know,
lose our lead.
That would be awful.
You're getting paranoid.
>> You are. You're sweating,
you're scaring yourself into
a panic out here.
You're not pulling...
>> I-I just want to make sure
one of us... Fine.
>> Rupert-- (laughs) there's a
reason that I've been doings a
Rupert strategical play for
him thus far because he needs
to be told where to vote by
someone he can really trust,
and let that be done.
So I just keep reminding him
of that, like, "Rupert, think
"about this a minute.
"Do you believe what Sandra
"told you or do you believe
the obvious truth?
I mean...
>> It's, it's smelling fishy.
>> If Sandra's story turns out
be true, and Russell did not
play the idol, then that means
I'm probably going home the
next Tribal Council.
I don't know.
Do I believe it?
Not a chance in the world.
But you never know in this game.
>> Russell looked me right in
the eye and swore on his kid's
life that he was with us.
And anybody that will do that,
right away I don't trust 'em.
>> Okay.
>> Okay, then don't
trust Russell.
>> About you?
>> About you.
>> They're gonna try to
vote me out.
>> Yeah, they want you gone.
Like, that's why I don't know
what to do 'cause it's weird,
Parvati.
Like, I have no power over here.
Like, everyone's freaked out
about you.
>> I don't know. I just...
So if I don't win today, then
they're voting for me?
>> Probably.
>> And Russell with probably
vote with them.
>> To get with Sandra?
>> Rid of Sandra.
>> Amanda and I got a chance to
talk for the first time sinceto
the merge, and I think I got
probably half her story.
So I haven't decided the best
plan yet because with her, I
don't know if she's telling me
the truth or not.
Will you tell me who everyone's
voting for?
>> Yeah.
>> Just at least tell me.
>> No, I will.
>> Okay. Do you swear you're
gonna be really honest with me?
>> Yes, I have been.
I told you all that stuff.
>> Okay, so then I have to
tell you something.
>> Okay.
>> You have another one?
>> Yeah.
>> How did you get another one?
>> I'm crafty. (laughs)
>> Love it. Loving it.
I had a conversation with
Parvati.
I didn't tell her everything,
but I told her enough to get
her to trust me, and she told me
that she had the idol.
And I like Parvati and
everything, but she makes it to
the end of this game, she's
gonna win again.
>> If we're working together,
then we're working together
and I trust you.
However the vote shakes down,
I'm gonna make sure my butt is
safe, no matter what.
But I'm gonna try to make it
work that none of our Villains
are going anywhere tonight.
>> But you trust me?
>> I trust you.
Should we do a secret handshake?
>> Yeah.
>> Blow it up.
(both laugh)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You're now merged as one tribe.
What's the new tribe name?
>> Uh, Yin Yang.
It means good and evil.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to your first
individual immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, first
things first, I will take back
the immunity idol.
Tribal immunity is no more.
Individual immunity is what
you seek.
For today's challenge, it's
very simple.
You will hold onto a pole for as
long as you can.
If you fall off, you're out
of the challenge.
Last person left hanging on
their pole wins immunity,
guaranteed a one-in-nine shot at
winning this game and the
million dollars.
Losers, Tribal Council.
Somebody will be going home.
Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for spots,
we'll get started.
All right, everybody climb up.
take your spots.
>> Oh, here we go.
It's kinda hot up here.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Geez.
>> Oh, my God, this is scary.
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> PROBST: And this challenge
is on.
Everybody finding their spot.
Amanda, Donaldson and Sandra
slowly inching down the post.
Could be a good strategy, could
be a sign they're in trouble.
J.T., Candice and Parvati have
all competed in this challenge
in previous seasons.
None of them have won this
challenge.
>> My leg won't stop shaking.
>> PROBST: Sandra already in
trouble seconds into this
challenge.
>> I can't get right.
>> Yeah, I hear ya.
You want to do it at the same
time?
One, two, three.
Donaldson steps down.
(Sandra groans)
Colby-- first person out of
this challenge.
Sandra steps down.
Sandra's now out of the
challenge.
Colby, disappointed how fast
you were out or is something
going on?
>> I knew, I knew it was gonna
be quick for me, yeah.
>> PROBST: How come?
>> Just based on that last
challenge we did with the
footholds.
Not my forte, that's for sure.
>> PROBST: We're down to eight.
We are one minute into this
challenge, and already, people
are struggling.
Rupert adjusting.
Very little room for your toes.
Candice, Danielle and Parvati
all look very solid.
Amanda looks very solid,
although she is low on
the post.
Russell trying to get
comfortable.
And Russell steps out of the
challenge.
Take a spot on the bench.
We are down to seven people left
in this challenge.
(Danielle exhales sharply)
(Rupert groans)
Rupert struggling.
Hanging on for dear life.
(Rupert groans)
Rupert is out of the challenge.
And we are down to six people
left in this challenge.
(Danielle exhales sharply)
Been up there just over
20 minutes.
Amanda steps out of the
challenge.
We are down to five people left
in this challenge.
(J.T. grunts)
>> Ah, you thought I was gone,
didn't you?
>> I was, like, "What"?
>> No, I was just getting
a little break.
>> PROBST: J.T., were you just
playing around?
>> No, I almost fell.
(Jerri, Danielle laugh)
>> PROBST: J.T. readjusting all
over the place now.
(J.T. groans)
J.T, drops out of the challenge
without warning.
>> Oh, I didn't see!
>> PROBST: We are now down to
four people left in this
challenge, and they are all
women.
Candice the lone remaining Hero.
(Parvati chuckles)
>> Geez, Parvati, how
in the heck are you staying on
like that?
Wow.
(Parvati chuckles)
I think I'm about done.
I can handle the pain,
It's the dehydration.
>> PROBST: Yeah, starting
to get to you?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Jerri moving down to
the lowest foothold.
Nowhere else to go.
Arms are shaking, legs
are shaking.
>> Good job.
>> PROBST: Jerri steps out of
the challenge after one hour,
30 minutes.
>> Good job, Jerri.
>> The bad thing is we drank
your water.
(Jerri laughs)
>> PROBST: We are now down
to three.
Candice and Parvati were in
their own showdown back in
the Cook Islands.
Danielle has never done
this challenge.
She's sitting right in between
the two of them.
Now been out here one
hour, 35 minutes.
>> All right, girls, good luck.
>> PROBST: What'd you say,
Candice?
You're stepping down?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Wow.
Before you step down, Candice,
I'm curious why in a challenge
for immunity in which of all the
people who've played it, you
lasted the longest.
You're the odds-on favorite
to win.
You're now-- for no reason--
just going to bow out of the
challenge.
>> They look like they could go
for a while.
It's true.
>> PROBST: Step out.
And with that, Candice steps off
the post and is out of
the challenge.
>> Good job, Candice.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: And we are now down
to two.
All the Heroes are gone.
>> How you doing?
>> I'm cool.
>> You're cool?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Two Villains left,
and immediately they start
to talk.
>> All right, this one's
all yours.
>> PROBST: Parvati appears to be
stepping out of this challenge,
and she does.
And with that, Danielle wins
first individual immunity.
(applause)
(Danielle grunts)
>> Good job, Danielle.
>> Nice, Danielle.
>> Thank you.
Yay!
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
Danielle safe tonight at
Tribal Council.
As for the rest of you, after
27 days, one of you going
home tonight.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's gonna be.
Head back to camp.
I'll see you at Tribal.
Congratulations.
>> Yes!
>> I think Parvati is gonna come
up with a hidden immunity idol
tonight.
But Parvati wouldn't have walked
off that pole, but I don't know.
That's all part of the plan
tonight; to see if I can oust
Russell for the weasel that
he is.
>> It's kinda strange how
Parvati stepped down at the end
of the challenge, you know?
And she's in such danger and she
knows it.
So the plans are, tonight,
the Heroes are gonna
let Russell write Parvati's name
down just to prove his loyalty
to all of of us.
Me and Candice and Rupert,
Amanda, Colby-- five strong--
will write down Sandra or
Jerri's name.
>> Right, yeah.
>> Sandra?
Jerri done a hell of a lot
better than Sandra did.
>> I don't even care
who goes home.
>> I don't either as long as
it's not me.
>> As long as it ain't us.
When we come back tonight,
they'll be real mad, like, "What
in the hell just happened?"
>> They think that they got this
in the bag.
Which tells me that Russell's
doing a good job of convincing
them.
>> When I first got here, I
tried to tell Rupert that
Russell is running this
whole show.
And anyway, we talked really,
really quick, and that was it.
I don't want my big mouth
to get me in trouble.
I still want Russell out bad.
But right now I'm stuck
with Russell.
I'm stuck with Russell.
>> My plan A is to give the idol
to Parvati, save herself,
and vote out J.T.
I don't have a plan B.
But I hope for the second time
I'm gonna save her with a
immunity idol.
I have a gift for you.
If it was just me, it'd be just
me, but I got to keep these
four girls on my Villain tribe
so I can get rid of J.T.
>> Oh, you!
You shouldn't have!
>> There you go.
(Parvati laughs)
Thanks, honey. (chuckles)
Russell just gave me his
immunity idol.
So that makes me safe for
for tonight.
And I have my own immunity
idol.
That also makes me safe
for the rest of the game.
It's like two little green men
protecting me.
And apparently everyone else
in this game is, like, desperate
to get rid of me.
And they said that I'm the most
dangerous player out here.
So I don't know.
I guess they're right.
I didn't really think they were
right until right now.
Now I really think they're
right. (chuckles)
>> What? Being on
separate tribes?
>> Yeah.
>> I know.
>> Because I honestly don't know
what to do.
I want to play with you, but I
don't see how we're gonna
play together.
So the idea is to have
Parvati play her idol and
vote out Sandra or Jerri.
It'll be really crazy tonight if
Parvati gives her idol to
to somebody.
I hope she doesn't.
I hope she plays it for herself
just so...
I mean, it's always good.
You never want idols floating
around.
It just ruins things.
She's so dangerous.
>> I just want to make sure
it's not me that goes.
Really?
>> Just play it.
>> Okay.
I knew that Amanda was lying to
me when she told me that they
were voting for me.
Like, I know you're trying to
get rid of me, but I'll just
play along with you right now.
It's, like, "Thanks for looking
"out for me (clicks tongue)
buddy."
>> Just to be safe.
>> Okay.
>> But, like...
>> I just, I don't know what to
do because I'm really honestly,
Parvati, I'm so confused, like.
>> It's gonna get messy,
so I think the best thing that
you could do tonight is just
let them vote for me, and just
vote with them.
Then we'll take it from there.
>> All right. (sighs)
My head hurts.
>> It's hard to really know who
they're voting for.
If they say they're voting me
out, and I play the idol, then
the idol's gone, and it's
just risky.
So damned if you do,
damned if you don't.
Unless, like, you picked
the right person.
I hope.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Coach and Courtney voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> PROBST: Rupert, what is camp
life like, both Heroes and
Villains living in the
same spot?
>> (laughs): It is...
an adjustment.
You know, you heard James say
the "banana etiquette" thing.
I haven't had a ripe banana
since... (laughs)
since they got here.
>> With all due respect,
there's so many plantains and
green bananas that I don't
think we should be penalized
for wanting to cook a plantain,
considering the plethora amount
that we have.
>> I don't think there's ever
been a discussion about eating
plantains.
We have a thousand plantains.
It's the ripe bananas.
We have ripe bananas all the
time, but we let them ripen.
>> But I always feel like I'm
walking on eggshells around the
camp, because you guys do things
your way, we've done them our
way, and now we've come
together, so we need to work out
a way where it works for
everybody.
>> I think... I think that, uh,
nothing's going to change.
There's two separate tribes.
The game is on.
Let's forget about the green
bananas and the yellow bananas
or whatever-- so what?
Let's play the game.
>> PROBST: Russell, could
tonight's vote dictate the rest
of the game?
>> Tonight's vote will dictate
the rest of the game.
This is the most important vote
that I've ever been a part of.
If one of the Villains go home,
then the Heroes are going to be
in the top five.
If one of the Heroes go home,
the Villains are going to be in
the top five.
That's just how it's going to
work tonight.
That's going to happen.
>> PROBST: J.T., sound true to
you?
>> I hope that it's true, and I
hope it's a Villain that goes
home, if it is.
>> PROBST: Was it a crazy day at
camp, J.T.?
>> None of these people want to
talk to me, so that leads me to
believe my name's getting
wrote down a lot tonight.
>> I'll talk to you anytime,
J.T.
>> My feelings are already hurt.
I don't want to hear it.
>> Aw! Maybe mine are hurt, too.
>> PROBST: Jerri, can you see
what J.T.'s talking about,
that you guys were somehow
avoiding him for some reason?
>> It did feel a little bit
like they had a wall up, J.T.
in particular.
>> Russell, is that maybe just
paranoia, that everybody's
feeling the same thing?
>> I think that that's exactly
what it is, paranoia.
You know, I talk to J.T. all the
time, all the time.
I've probably been talking to
their tribe more than mine.
>> PROBST: Sandra, concern you a
little, Russell, your Villain
tribe mate, is over there making
friends with the Heroes?
>> No. I mean, we all want
to get along.
I mean, I talk to everyone
individually, "Hey, how you
doing, where you from, where
you work," whatever, but as far
as strategy, nobody said
nothing to me neither, so I
didn't say nothing to them
neither.
>> I feel like everyone's been
avoiding me.
(laughs): I feel like a leper on
this tribe. I do.
>> PROBST: But is that just
because you're used to getting
attention all the time in life?
(laughter)
>> No, Jeff, but you're right.
But no.
I think... I think it's because
everyone thinks I'm such a
threat, and so no one wants to
be associated with me.
>> PROBST: So you believe the
Heroes have you in their sights
tonight?
>> Definitely.
>> Or maybe we haven't
approached Parvati yet because
we know she's going to be
around for a few more days and
we'll have that opportunity.
So there's another angle.
>> So in other words, the
Heroes might be targeting
somebody else on the Villains.
>> Maybe.
>> J.T., has there been any
talk in your group about who
might have any hidden immunity
idols, if there are any in the
game at all?
>> The idols are a big topic of
conversation.
It's a mess, and I don't have
any idea who might have an idol
or who's got one.
I know I don't have one, so I'm
pretty worried about it.
>> PROBST: Parvati, topic of
discussion on the Villains'
tribe?
>> Yeah, definitely.
I mean, we've seen what idols
can do, as far as on the
Villain tribe.
It broke a completely solid
alliance and turned the game.
>> PROBST: Well, I don't think
we've had a bigger vote.
Danielle, you have the immunity
necklace.
I assume you're keeping it
tonight.
>> Of course.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Danielle.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Russell, you're up.
>> You seem like a real cool
guy, but it was a real dumb
move by giving me your idol.
And because of that, I gotta
vote you out tonight.
>> This is my love letter to
you.
Since you tried to vote me out,
I figured I should return the
favor.
>> Hoping my name doesn't come
up tonight.
>> I hope Parvati plays that
idol and shows everybody that
Russell is a liar.
>> Jerri, we're voting for you
tonight because if there is an
immunity idol, you're the least
likely person that they would
give it to.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
>> You know what, Jeff?
(others groaning)
I think it would be downright
depressing to sit and watch
green bananas turn yellow
without my debaucherous little
Villains, so...
Sandra, that's for you.
>> Get out of here! For real?
>> Yeah.
And, Jeff...
I would just like to increase
our odds.
So, Jerri, that one's for you,
too.
>> PROBST: Thanks, Jerri,
Sandra.
>> Wow!
>> PROBST: The rules of Survivor
state that if anybody plays a
hidden immunity idol, then any
votes cast against that person
will not count.
These are both hidden immunity
idols.
Any votes cast for Sandra or
Jerri will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Jerri.
Does not count.
J.T.
One vote J.T.
That's two votes J.T.
11th person voted out and the
third member of our jury...
J.T.
That's three, and tonight
that's enough.
J.T., the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> Good luck, fellas.
>> PROBST: Well, in a game full
of crazy moves, that was one of
the craziest.
With tonight's vote, it
certainly appears that the
Villains have the upper hand,
but you know better than
anybody-- anything can and
probably will still happen in
this game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> Whatever, whatever.
>> PROBST: As Russell loses
control of his alliance...
>> You lied to me.
>> How did I lie to you?
>> PROBST: ... Sandra takes
control of the game.
>> They're done.
So you want Russell gone?
>> Yeah.
>> Russell's gone.
My target is Russell.
I've been waiting to take him
down for 30 days.
>> Yeah, I trust you.
(Sandra laughs)
>> I feel like a total idiot
right now.
It's pretty terrible to be
voted out by your own idol.
I felt like Russell would vote
the way we told him to vote.
People are Villains for a
reason-- don't ever trust them.
Worse than that, don't ever
trust women, ever, ever, ever.
You can't always win.
It was a big move, do or die,
and I died tonight.