Previously on anytime survivor."
Over the past 10 years, some of
"Survivor's" Memorable castaways
Played the game with honor and Instigate.
in my world, I've always
Tried to show that good will w Win.
While others relied on ruthless
Cunning and backstabbing.
I'm the original villaines of
"Survivor" And I have to tell
You I feel like mother teresa
Right now with these people.
In the historic,
20th season of "Survivor" 10
Of the most notorious villains
Have returned to face 10 of the Greatest heroes.
Russell has the bag for the Villains!
The first challenge was a fierce Battle.
The heroes suffered two Injuries.
my shoulder.
my toe is broke.
But ultimately Prevailed.
Heroes win reward!
Filled with confidence, the
Heroes worked well together and Built a solid camp.
I love my tribe.
We have a good aura.
We have good energy.
But not every hero
Acted heroically.
J.T. Dipped to the villains'
Playbook and formed conflicting Alliances.
I'm going to form alliances With everyone I can.
It's going to be a whole
Different ballgame for me.
At the villains'
Beach boston rob is the only one Who worked.
they don't want to build a Shelter.
They don't want to try to get a Fire going.
There's noble here that wants to
Do anything.
Unbeknownst to rob,
Russell was very busy.
we're going to be better of a
Pair that you can possibly Imagine. I agree.
Up to his old tricks
Making secret deals and daniel And poofortd.
are russell I definitely feel
Like I am making a deal with the
Devil but I want the devil on my Side.
And coach was making
Gallant advances towards jerri.
jerri and I, we have a little Connection.
Survivors ready? Go!
come on, heroes!
At the immunity Challenge,
the heroes opened a Huge lead.
Heroes look like they've been
Paddling together forever!
When they got to the puzzle,
Things changed.
Heroes still trying to figure
Out the first piece of this Puzzle.
maybe just two different Pieces.
Sugar and amanda were
Unable to work together,
Allowing the villains to pull Ahead.
Villains win first immunity Challenge!
At tribal council, the heroes
Unanimously voted to make sugar
Pay for her poor performance at
The challenge.
Sugar, the tribe has spoken.
And now both tribes are facing
Tough questions: Did the heroes
Make the right choice to Strengthen their tribe?
As for the villains, with
Torrential sea storms on the
Way, will the lack of shelter
Zap their strength and kill any
Chance of futur victories?
Paradise, my ass!
man, this is worse underneath
Here than it is out here.
Pouring down rain, like, five
People were ready to die.
so cold.
everybody's crying, and I
Can't take it any more.
The main thing we should be
Doing is trying to make a fire
And trying to get our shelter Good.
Nobody wants to step up and they
Want to sit in the rain night
After night, and it's making me
Physically sick, you know.
unbelievable, man.
I am soaked through and through.
it's like, again, again,
Again I'm on the buffoon tribe. Again.
I was on mar kasich, I was on,
On all-stars and again now.
don't know what I'm going To do.
this is-- this is rough.
People are freaking out.
I mean, there's a lot of
Complaining last night.
it's going to get worse.
I know, and it's only day Four.
it's all going to come down
To what people got upstairs.
yup.
That's what rob said.
He said, "Here we go.
It's the beginning."
so here we are on day four on
At least design four, probably
Design five of the shelter.
The first one was the best, and
The strongest and Semi-leak-proof.
And each subsequent shelter gets
Worse and worse and worse, and
Now we're-- we're doing it aga Again.
it's going to come up in the
Back, and it's going to come
Down in the front, right, like a Lean-to.
We're stopping, like, about Three feet.
I think we should keep it low
Like that, don't you?
I think we should just--
I think we should keep it low
And put the roof on.
let them do what they want to Do.
I don't think we should Complain... Parvati.
I'm not complaining.
I'm just putting-- saying an Opinion. never mind.
I got it.
boston rob is like the
Bright, shining star, and he
Jets so frustrated with these Foolz.
I hope he doesn't drop dead in
The next few days because we'll All die.
There's no way around it.
You don't need to make this Like-- reinforced.
I thought we didn't have a Lot of time.
this is not good.
oh, there's the leaves.
well, this row and that row's
Going to cover all that.
we're at the hereose' camp.
We're a bunch of professional
And seasoned "Survivors."
We're some of the best
"Survivors" Ever, the greatest.
let colby cut that one.
Just mark it and y'all know how Big you'll need them.
man, I love a working tribe.
I know, isn't that nice? yes.
even people that know what
They're doing.
Should we make coconut or what Do you think?
roasted coconut?
yeah.
yeah, popcorn.
let's do that.
stephenie.
For my game, it is a very good
Idea for me to get rid of steph.
I mean, she's a sweet girl, but
In the game, I think stephenie
Would side with anyone that got
Her one day further.
brown it a little more like
That one, right?
you want it to get crispy.
it's sticking pretty bad.
you're doing popcorn
Different than I ever did it, So.
Cook it dry and turn it around
In the sea salt.
See the white on the side,
That's assault? I don't know.
You're the cook.
rupert-- is starting to get a
Little bit annoying.
Every time I turn around, he's
Got an opinion about everything.
Like the coconut.
isn't that good?
that's good.
when you make them little,
Teeny chunks, your saliva mixes
In with them enough that you
Don't taste the hole as much and It's popcorn.
I'm just sitting back and
Being quiet because he could be
Trying to get me out of this Game.
I honestly think the guy is
Playing up the good guy role out Here.
And he is a good guy.
I'm not saying he's not, but
It's just-- you know, it's
Overkill right now.
It's day four, like, whoa.
we're going to tie each
Individual one to this.
no.
I need some more water.
The shelter sucks.
It's terrible.
And you know what I should have
Done from day one, say, "Listen,
You have to listen to me.
This is the way we're going to Do it.
If you don't like it, that's Fine.
I'll mark you down and I'll vote
You off first."
I didn't want to be a dictator
This time around.
I wanted to be the diplomat.
Look where that got me-- running
In circles.
I mean, they got me.
They got me good.
They whipped me.
And I just-- it, like, hit me.
I said that's enough.
It's over. It's done.
That's it.
so no more house?
no more.
I'm done.
You get me, right?
You feel me? I understand.
It's frustrating.
poarks god, why!
Why can't we have james and
Colby and rupert?
how did they get every, like,
Awesome guy, and we got randy!
are things going to get
Better at all before they get
Worse?
what's rob doing?
Why did he walk away?
I don't know.
I think everybody's kind of
Having a meltdown.
Not everybody.
A lot of us are, but I'm not.
rob?
Hey, rob?
Rob?
Talk to me.
Rob.
Talk to me. What's going on?
Can you just open your eyes,
Please? Please, rob, come on.
Just look at me.
Your head hurts?
yeah.
what do you want me to do?
get help.
all right. I'll be right back.
Okay?
I saw the whole thing, and it
Really scared me.
I mean, I don't want to see
Anybody get hurt.
This is-- this is where
"Survivor" Gets serious because
It involves your life beyond the
Game, and without rob here, it's
Going to really hurt us.
We're going to slowly spiral
Down into a big pit of
Negativity, which I know is only
Going to get worse.
all right, we've got the
Medical team here now.
We're going to see how you are.
Can you open your eyes for us?
Rob, you can hear
Me?
Rob?
Coming up next ...
You can hear me?
hey.
I feel like... It's getting
The best of me.
Rob, you can hear me?
What's the problem?
140 over 70.
I've got some water for you, Mate?
Can you lift your hand up and
Porthe water in yourself?
the funny thing about being
Unconscious is you don't Remember anything.
I remember feeling really sick
And I thought I had to sit down,
And the next thing I remember
There was a doctor or somebody
Was talking and I heard jeff Probst talking.
In terms of giving an
Overall assessment, he looks
Worse than he is.
at the moment that's what we Think.
There's nothing we found on
Examining him that would concern Us.
Okay.
So you were definitely-- you
Were out.
I feel better, though.
Good.
You look a lot better right now.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
E-why are you sorry?
it's just... I feel like...
It's getting the best of me.
And I love and respect it too
Much.
To not play, you know. yeah.
I want to win this game,
Dude. Watch this.
When I finally came to, I had a
Moment of clarity, and that was
Stop trying to be the good guy.
Because I'm trying to be so
Good, I physically made myself Sick.
Just do what everybody wants you
To d and be the villain.
You want a hand Getting up?
yeah, dude.
there was no way I was going To leave.
I mean, "Survivor" Is my life.
I love the game.
It's given me so much, and
There's no way I would ever Quit.
The doctors checked me out and
Basically told me I had the flu,
Maybe a little bit of case of
Cry babyitis.
You it's not easy.
It's been six years.
I just have to start smacking Them into shape.
Mariano's back.
yeah.
You're on your own.
okay.
what's happening, man?
I got real sick.
I was worried.
I've been having these Migraines, man.
And I think with the heat and
The exhaustion and everything,
It just got the best of me.
And that's it.
I should be good in 48 hours.
I was just telling-- I was just
Telling ... Boston rob came ba Bab-- back.
He's not out of the game.
Everything's cool.
Even though I'm the villain, I
Still-- I still worry a little
Bit about stuff like that.
Besides he's strong.
He gives us a better shot to win
The challenge.
Come on in, guys!
Villains getting your first look
At the new hero tribe.
Sugar voted out at the last
Tribal council.
Guys ready to get to today's
Immunity challenge?
First things first--
Take it back, jerri.
Immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, on my
"Go," Two members of each tribe
Will race to roll a large,
Tribe-colored crate back to your Platform.
Then the next two go.
Once you've collected all six
Crate, you must use them to
Build a staircase that will
Spell out your tribe name.
First tribe to stack their
Craits correctly and get all
Their tribe members to the top
Wins immunity, safe from the Vote.
Losers go to tribal council,
Where the second person will be
Voted out from this game.
In addition to immunity, are you
Also playing for reward.
man!
Tarp, rope, nails.
Should help keep you dry out Here.
History on this challenge--
J.T., coach, and tyson, all
Played this challenge in their Season.
You're on opposite tribes today.
See how it plays out.
Because it runs in pairs, we
Need to even up the tribes.
That means, villains, you're
Sitting out two people.
Who's it going to be?
courtney.
Randy and courtney
Are sitting out.
Heroes you're sitting out one Person.
Who is it going to be?
I guess I'm sitting out.
You don't look happy, Rupert.
I don't want that I can run
As well with a broken toe.
Rupert sitting out
For the heroes.
I'll give you a minute to
Strategize and we'll get Started.
it's going to be, like, our
Last immunity challenge with the
Puzzle at the end.
We have to win today, bottom Line.
If we lose, we're in bad shape.
that's right, one voice. yes.
that's right. okay.
Here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's j.T. And cirie for the
Heroes.
Danielle and boston rob for the
Villains.
J.T. And cirie doing a good job
Straight down the course.
Rob and danielle a little off
Course.
These craits are very heavy.
Once your crate hits the
Platform, the next two had head Out.
Go, heroes.
To.Rob and danielle really slowg
Down at the end.
Sandra and tyson heading out now
For the villains.
Cand expas tom increasing the
Lead for the heroes.
come otom!
one more!
Go, heroes!
Colby and stephenie heading out
For the heroes.
Heroes are holding on to a
One-crate lead.
Gerry and coach heading out for
The villains while colby and
Stephenie head back with the
Third crate for the heroes.
Go, here'soze.
Heroes have three crates back.
Vill wans two.
Coach and jerri heading back
With that third crate for the Villains.
come on, you gotta push it Again!
I am!
James and amanda
Heading back with the fourth
Crate for the heroes.
There are six total.
Russell and parvati out on the Course.
James just walking that crate Back.
J.T. And tom heading out for
That fifth crate for the heroes.
Rul and parvati trying to get
Back with that fourth crate for The villains.
come oparvati! Push, parvati!
You got it, you got it!
Russell and parvati
Back with the fourth crate.
Now they're sending out their
Big guns.
Once everybody has gone once, Anybody can go.
Rob and tyson have some time it
Make up for the villains.
keep it up!
Rob and tyson back
Finally with that fifth crate
For the villains.
Russell and coach heading out
For that sixth and final crate.
James and coil bee heading back
With their sixth and final Crate.
beautiful!
It's like a ball rolling down
That aisle!
Go!
Start working on your puzzle,
Heroes.
straight to the wall,
Straight to the wall.
yeah, russell!
good job, guys.
Go, villains!
Start working on your puzzle.
You're building a stai case.
Your name will be visible along Both sides.
come on, everybody.
Quickly getting a plan together.
we need a piece with just
This part of the "H" And an "E."
The last challenge
Was decided by a puzzle, and the
Villains won.
Heroes looking for some
Redemption in this challenge.
yes, yes!
This is right!
This is right, guys.
now pull it up.
Once again, boston
Rob is leading his tribe through
The puzzle portion of this Challenge.
it's not right.
I know.
This is the bottom!
pick it up.
J.T. Leading the
Heroes.
flip it back one time.
perfect!
The villains are
Getting closer and closer.
perfect.
Heroes' lead has been Evaporated.
come on.
You gotta work. You gotta work.
come on, we gotta hustle,
Guys. come on, guys.
This is not it. this is it.
this one?
where's-- lift block!
villains trying to make a big
Move now, trying to lift that Crate up.
watch out, watch out!
Without crushing each
Other.
Heroes slow and steady but
Making a lot of moves.
It's russell and coach lifting.
Rob pushing.
Heroes still working.
Both tribes are in this.
roll it!
Villains in a very
Precarious position but they Have it up.
Good team work.
cea can't do that again.
good job, rob.
rob!
we need an "R."
Where is the "R?"
the "R" Is here.
this isn't right.
come on, you guys!
You guys gotta move!
this is it, j.T.
I said that in the beginning.
Villains are very
Close.
here we go!
Just get it up!
that's not-- is that right?
that's not right, that's not Right.
Get it back down.
Get it where it was.
guys move this over here.
Coordinate. what?
it's not right.
It's not right.
we all need to listen. One voice.
Heroes now starting To get frustrated.
what are we doing?
straight up.
Villains have one
Piece left but it's got to come
All the way to the top.
somebody push this towards Me.
spin it what way towards tom.
no, no, this is not right.
yeah.
shut up!
Heroes talking trash
To each other.
Not a good sign.
drop it!
we got it!
We got it!
Villains think they Have it.
Get to the top, villains.
Villains win the second immunity
Challenge in a row!
let's go home and just Collapse, dude.
you gotta have one voice, Y'all.
He was telling you all what to Do.
we were listening.
no, you were not.
he was telling you what to
Do.
Everybody's mouth wants to talk.
One voice.
james, I don't care who you
Are, I don't care where you're
At, you just don't talk to People like that.
The problem is I can't say
Anything because rupert already
Has it out for me, for whatever Reason.
Maybe I threaten his popularity,
I don't know. So I'm just trying to say as Little as possible.
Villains,
Congratulations once again.
Two challenges, two victoryes.
good job, guys.
Villains grab your
Tarp, rope, nails.
Head on back to camp.
good job, guys.
peace out.
Heroes, going to be
An interesting afternoon as for
The second time in a row, you
Guys will lose somebody at Tribal council.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at tribal.
stephenie has been only
Person in "Survivor" History to
Lose every person in her tribe
To where she's the only one Left.
You know, she's, obviously, the Problem.
There's no other source of
Kryptonite in here to suck all
The super heroes' powers but Her.
It's like, wow, you need to go Home.
the challenge really sucked Today.
The last time we failed on the
Puzzle, no one really stepped Up.
And this time I said, "Hey, I've
Done this challenge before.
I'll be the man to run the Puzzle."
But there were a few people
Hohad to say, "No, please,
Please, listen to me."
It would have been a lot easier
If people had been listening
Instead of telling me what to Do.
Look I stepped up to the puzzle.
We didn't win.
I take responsibility.
nobody was listening.
boston rob is great at Puzzles.
He ideal and screamed at his Team.
He told them to shut up.
They all listened to him, and he Won.
I could have told-- I could
Have told everybody to shut up,
Too, and I didn't.
I just wanted everybody to be
Quiet and pay attention to what
That guy had to say. Pfs important.
we have to check our egos at
The door and follow who we
Designate to be the best job for
The challenge. one voice.
That's all I ask for is one damn Voice.
Then I get defensive people.
And then I get people telling
Everybody they're one.
I don't want to hear that.
One voice next time.
That's the only way we get to
The top.
We shut up and listen to the guy
That's done the challenge.
If you're defensive, you're Wrong.
There are going to be other
Challenges like this, and we
Need to focus.
Because I ain't never lost this
Much in my life.
That's all I'm saying.
This is ridiculous.
You need to suck it up.
that panicked scream and
Anguish cry of james when he got
Back to the hut, you know, all Right, great.
You've been a winner your whole Life?
I doubt it.
I'd love to tell him what a
Winner is and what a loser and
Where he fits into that-- that Equation.
And once again, I've got to hold
My tongue and not respond to
That, that kills me out here.
we have a tarp!
the most exciting moment.
it matches my outfit.
winning the challenge today
Was awesome, not only because we
Avoid tribal but also because we
Got a tarp.
Hats off to boston rob.
who loves you, baby?
I got something for you.
boston rob worked his ass off
In the challenge today.
No question about it. I respect that.
it's the elusive giant clam.
Do you want to touch it?
I don't know. I'm afraid.
come on.
You can touch my clam.
nice work, rob.
boston rob thinks that he's In charge.
I'm starting to think this just
Ain't working out.
I didn't know his personality
Was that strong.
But you know what?
This is where I'm in charge.
I am king russell.
From samoa.
wooo-hoo!
I got a chicken, baby.
we can make chicken soup.
we got a chicken.
They trying to catch fish.
You gotta catch real food.
her teams don't ever win.
Think about it.
She's made it to the end by Herself.
She was the only person left on The entire tribe.
You mean to tell me, that's good Luck?
Obviously, not.
Something just ain't right, and
It got to be her.
if they get rid of me over
Amanda and we've already lost Two?
you're in a bad spot, my Friend.
I know it.
this is the only girl who's
Made it to the end as one pers Person.
She's nullified her whole tribe
Until she was the last one left. yup.
it got to be her.
this is a lot different than
Our first.
Everyone was okay with sugar Going home.
She was not a part of any solid
Alliance.
So now, we're lking at a whole
Different ballgame because after
Tonight, I'm in one alliance in
This game.
I can either go with james,
Rupert, and amanda and bring
Sire and candace along.
Or I can go with colby, tom, and
Stephenie, and bring candace and Cirie along.
So one thing I do know, we're
Going to piss a few people off.
we should have won that, Rupe. it's okay.
It's as much my fault as any for
Not pushin push harder to be ine Challenge.
rupert's over there talking To j.T. Now.
right.
yeah, they're all--
they're all-- we're the three
On the outs.
It's all on the line today.
We know what we're up against.
And I'm not-- I don't have any
False illusions of loyalty from
From j.T. At this point.
This is the way it's going to
Be-- the order's going to be Stephenie, me, you.
We have to convince candace and
Cirie that the order's going to
Be stephenie, cirie, candace.
If I can get cirie and candace
To switch over with our
Three-some, send amanda home,
Then we're controlling this Game.
so, the plan is to get rid of
The weakest first, so that would
Help us if we got rid of amanda.
The problem with that plan is we
Don't know if j.T. Is with us or Not.
So if tom, colby, and myself can
Pull in cirie and candace, maybe
I am safe and we're going to get
Our five strong and come out of
This all right tonight.
But I can guarantee that you're Next. right.
I can promise you that.
Either you or cirie, if we have
To go to another tribal council,
And then whoever's left.
And I think we've got a better
Deal for you.
this vote today is crucial
Because the line will be drawn
In the sand, and you'll be on
One side or the other.
And I feel like I'm on the
Bottom of either alliance.
So I'm, like, which way do I go?
Which way is it worse? I don't know.
I'm really not in a good
Position anyway, you know what I Mean?
I think you're in the Position.
I think you're the swing vote Tonight.
everybody wants me to vote,
You know, one way tonight.
But... What about me down the Road, you know? right.
I mean, I really got to think
What's best for me. yup.
So one assurance you would have,
They all go home before you ever Go home.
You're not going to get that Deal on their side. yup.
I'm not even going to ask you
What you're going to do.
You and cirie are going to have
To decide if this is a move that
Makes sense to you.
Tom, colby, stephenie, are
Writing amanda's name down.
I'm trusting me gut on this, and
I think you should trust your
Gut on this, too and see where
It takes you.
all right, so what's the Deal?
tell me everything.
What's going on? I just want to do what's be Best.
Ultimately best for the long
Run, for now.
The problem with this decision
Is once this decision is made,
All the cards are out.
I know you guys are all
Tight, and I don't know, like,
Any of you guys from before, and
All that stuff--
see, that's the problem.
I don't know why everybody
Thinks we're so tight.
Yeah, me and amanda made it to
The end, but amanda chose
Parvati over me.
Amanda cost me a million Dollars.
So it's not like that.
I need somebody that I can Trust.
so do I.
and I don't really have
Anything else going for me.
hello.
so, I mean--
I think we have some common
Denominators.
so who goes first?
I don't know.
Honestly, as long as it's not
Us, it don't much matter to me.
J.T., the group of
Misfit villains, taking the
Heroes to the cleaners.
it's pretty embarrassing.
I stepped up today and didn't
Come through so I feel bad about That.
No one was listening.
And I notice on the villains
Boston rob telling everyone to
Shut up, and maybe I should have Done that.
James, you were as
Frustrated as I've seen you in
Playing this game three times.
there should have only been
One voice talking, and there Wasn't.
And I'm trying to make sure
Everybody is being quiet, and
There was a certain individual
Who voiced out their opinion
That they were being quiet.
So who was that?
stephenie.
I said, everybody shut up."
"Oh, I'm not talking."
that was after the challenge Was over. yes.
you looked at me and said,
"Hey, y'all."
darling, your name is not Y'all.
I'll be damned if there's
Anybody named y'all in here.
you're trying to blame the
Entire challenge on me.
baby, it's not about you, no
Matter how much you want to be
And how much you want crave it
To be you, it's not you.
I asked the question, and the
Person who usually tries to
Cover their back, they're the
One that has to.
You've been on the tribe where
You lost your entire team.
It was very romantic that you
Survived all your teammates on
Your tribe--
james, this isn't about me.
I thought you said it wasn't
About me let's get this rolling.
james, you just attacked her
And expect her to sit here and
Not defend herself.
You just total probst that there
Was one person who causedut the
Challenge today.
Now you're getting back to her
Past season.
Just let it be, bro.
the two of you all, how about That one?
Is that good enough.
make it the three of them All. Okay?
Alliances have been made. Divisions have been cast in the Tribe.
You repeating things and just
Bullying people until they Back--
I'm not bullying people.
you were bullying stiff me. I was not.
jeff asked who you were
Speaking about and you said her Name.
That does mean her.
That doesn't mean y'all.
That means stephenie.
if you walk up to somebody
And say I wasn't doing nothing,
Usually they're doing something.
maybe in your world, james.
I don't know.
I don't live in your world.
Anyway... this is unbelievable.
Colby, this has to be
Terribly alarming.
We're on day six.
I had no idea it would shift
From that team mentality to the
Self-preservation this early.
Stephenie, how
Concerned are you about past
Relationships in this game?
Worried that it could work
Against that you played with Tom?
oh, yeah. Absolutely.
I mean, yeah, we're friends.
But, I played against him and
Merged with him, and he cut my
Throat in the end.
Cirie, you, amanda,
And james all played together.
What do you do to deflect that?
like stephenie said, she
Played with tom, and tom cut her
Throat in the end.
The same thing kind of happened
With me and amanda at the very End.
Amanda chose parvati over me.
So if you think that's the route
I would want to take again,
Obviously, you don't know me.
Amanda, how concerned
Are you that your past
Relationship are going to come Back to haunt you?
legitimately concerned.
Because, you know, I've been
Hearing my name bounced around,
And it's alarming.
You know, you get really Nervous.
And you just hope you make the
Right choices and the right
Alliances and that's all you can
Do.
All right, it is time
To vote.
Rupert, you're up.
it's the plan.
You're the weakest.
I'll go tally the
Votes.
Once the votes are read, the
Decision is final.
The person voted out will be
Asked to leave the tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, stef.
Amanda.
One vote steph, one vote amanda. Steph.
That's two votes steph, one vote
Amanda. Amanda. We're tied.
Two votes steph, two votes
Amanda. Steph.
That's three votes steph, two
Votes amanda. Amanda. Tied again.
Three votes steph, three votes Amanda. Steph.
That's four votes steph, three
Votes amanda.
Second person voted out of
Heroes vs. Villains,"
Stephenie. That's five. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Steph, the tribe has spoken.
some advice, next time y'all
Lose a challenge, a little less
Cursing off your tribe might Help.
keep your mouth shut.
come on.
it's been a pleasure.
I think tonight's
Tribal council speaks for Itself.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Drive one.
jeff: Stay tuned for scenes From our next episode. Next time on "Survivor":
told you you are on the wrong Team, james.
a hero spiralout of control.
james got to bring down the
Nasty, brutish, bullying.
I just want to win, y'all.
it's an ugly situation.
you could have been gentler.
I am upset that I'm out of The game.
Take comfort in knowing that
They definitely made the wrong
Move by getting rid of me.
These people don't even
Genuinely try to get to know Each other.