>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Heroes, for the second time in a
row, you guys will lose somebody
at Tribal Council.
By day six, the Heroes had lost
two challenges and were beaten
and demoralized.
>> If we don't become a cohesive
team, we will continue to lose.
>> PROBST: Things were so bad
that some of the Heroes started
to behave like villains.
James bullied the tribe.
>> One voice.
That's all I ask.
Then I get people telling
everybody they're wrong.
>> PROBST: And J.T. was equally
villainous.
>> I'm going to form alliances
with everyone I can.
My strategy is to keep everyone
on my side, man.
>> PROBST: He made conflicting
deals with both James and Tom.
At the Villains' camp, Rob's
heroic actions made him the de
facto tribe leader.
>> You are the man, and it's
like, when you're talking, I'm
just hanging on every word.
>> I appreciate it.
>> Rob thinks he's the boss of
the camp, but this is my
mountain and I'm still the king
of the hill.
>> PROBST: Russell got fed up
with his tribe following Rob and
staged a rebellion by hiding the
machete.
>> Getting rid of the machete
will cause conflict in this
camp, and that's a good thing.
>> PROBST: Go!
>> Tom, get him!
>> Yeah!
Go, go!
>> PROBST: But at the last
immunity challenge, everything
changed.
Heroes win!
The Heroes destroyed the
Villains in a huge blowout.
In addition to immunity, you
have coffee, sugar.
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
Sandra called out Coach for
being lazy.
>> Coach'll delegate, "You do
this and I'll do this and we'll
go do that," but then when you
look, Coach is gone two miles
out.
>> PROBST: But in the end, the
entire tribe voted out their
oldest and most abrasive member.
Randy, the tribe has spoken.
Now, if the Villains can't get
their act together, the Heroes
will even the score.
17 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Sandra tried to call me out
in Tribal tonight, and it was
just very disheartening.
I'm human, I'm sensitive.
I'm probably more sensitive
than most people.
I just hide it behind a lot of
things that I've done and
accomplished and behind a lot of
machismo.
What did I do to deserve Sandra
saying that tonight?
There's never been somebody like
me out here and there's never
going to be anybody like me
again.
All of this, man, I don't need
it.
I'm ... the man, and I don't
need anybody to tell me or
validate that.
I'm the only person out here
that will not ... compromise.
(Coach clears throat)
>> I understand where you're
coming from, dude.
>> It's unbelievable, man.
Why doesn't anybody ever say
anything good about me?
Am I that bad of a person, man?
Nobody ever does, man.
I'm sensitive.
>> Coach, I know you're
sensitive, dude.
>> But, dude...
>> If you want to stick it out,
I'll help you through it.
>> Thanks for coming out here,
man.
>> No problem, dude.
Just let me know how I can help.
I promise you.
>> Like what?
>> Don't wear feathers in your
hair at Tribal.
Don't tell your stories.
People don't believe your
stories.
They mock you.
There's no reason to tell them.
And do your tai chi in private
where nobody can see you.
>> Coach pulled me aside and
said he wanted to go home, but
the Villains do need Coach in
the game.
I mean, he's, he's much, much
stronger than the last time he
played physically, and that's
what we need right now.
>> I'm telling you, dude, I
don't care what anybody says.
>> When we got back from Tribal
Council, Coach broke down in
tears and said he didn't think
the game deserved his nobility,
and he wanted to quit the game,
so I told him to stick in there
and he knew what he was getting
into.
It's not like any of us are
Survivor virgins.
>> Is he okay, Tyson?
>> He's sad.
He talked to me last night and
said he was really thinking
about just going home.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
He cried.
He was, like, sobbing.
>> I can't believe that.
This morning has been a little
bit of an attitude shift.
Coach had a little sob session
with Tyson, wanted to quit the
game or something.
I don't know.
That's not much of a coach, if
you ask me.
What was that all about, man?
>> It's just I feel like I'm on
the outside.
I want to bond with you, but I
feel like you started playing
the game...
>> I'm gonna tell you something
right now.
You're not on the outside.
Okay?
I'm gonna tell you that.
We're good.
Look it, it's going to be okay,
for real, man.
Come here.
I know you're hurting.
It's all right.
>> I want-- I mean, I, like,
want to, like, sharpen each
other out here.
I want to, like, do stuff
together.
>> Then you're going to have to
trust me.
Like, literally trust me, and
you're going to be fine.
All right?
>> But I feel like the only time
you, like, want to bond with me
is when we're getting up for the
challenges, which is cool, and
if that's all you want...
>> I'm not gonna say anymore.
I'm gonna say you have to trust
me.
And it's all about this island,
all right, so don't worry about
it.
Don't sweat it, man, and pick
your ... head up and act like a
man, for real.
All right?
>> All right.
I'm different than most people.
I'm one of a kind.
The last of the Mohicans, King
Arthur-- a legend.
Nobody out here has got what I
have.
Confucius says that the greatest
glory a man can have is not in
never falling but in rising
again every time he falls, and I
fell hard last night.
You got to be weak to be strong.
There's power in weakness.
Today's challenge, you'll see an
even fiercer warrior from me.
>> Yay!
>> All right.
>> Whoo!
>> Read it, read it.
>> "Choose from this mountain
of goods,
Some items to help you improve
your life."
>> Yeah.
>> "Work like a well-oiled
machine,
To alleviate your hardships and
strife."
>> It's the catalog!
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> "Sears: Life. Well Spent."
>> Oh, my God.
>> Yeah, I love that.
>> Yes!
>> What does it say-- how many
we can pick?
>> Two items.
>> Fishing kit.
>> Oh!
>> Yes!
>> We kind of proved at the last
challenge that we're serious
about this now and we're more
united, and I think it's changed
us as a tribe.
So if the Villains walk away
with this Sears stuff, I'm going
to be mad because I don't want
to lose momentum.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Heroes getting your first look
at the new Villain tribe.
Randy voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you are going to race
head to head as you slide down a
slippery course to retrieve a
numbered ball that I will
randomly assign each round.
Once you have the ball, toss it
in your basket.
First person to get their ball
in their basket scores a point
for their tribe.
First tribe to four wins reward.
Let's get to the reward.
This morning, in your treemail,
you received a Sears circular
with a ton of products to choose
from.
Heroes, you chose a well-
equipped tackle box and a
fishing pole and the kitchen
set-- everything you need to
catch food, cook food.
Villains, you went a different
route-- a very full tool kit,
along with a tarp, twine, and a
multifunction tool-- everything
you guys need to build, I'm
guessing, a better shelter.
All right, Villains, you're
sitting out one person.
It must be a woman.
Keep in mind you cannot sit out
the same person at back-to-back
challenges.
>> I'll sit out.
>> PROBST: All right, Parvati,
take a spot on the bench.
Draw for matchups, get started.
All right, here we go.
First round-- Coach for the
Villains, taking on Tom Westman
for the Heroes.
You are looking for number 14.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Both guys get a good run.
Both guys launch themselves.
A little bit of a battle.
Tom has his.
Coach has his.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Coach in and out for
the Villains.
Tom just misses.
Coach scores for the Villains!
Villains lead 1-zip.
Next round-- Russell for the
Villains, taking on Cirie for
the Heroes.
You're going for number nine.
Survivors ready?
Go.
The more speed, the further you
will go.
Russell not messing around.
Grabs his ball, and he is off.
Cirie having to crawl on her
hands and knees to get to the
number nine.
Russell with a big advantage
now.
A lot of extra time, more shots.
Cirie still not here.
>> That's it.
>> PROBST: Russell scores for
the Villains.
Villains lead 2-zip.
>> Good job, Russ.
>> PROBST: Next two-- for the
Villains, Courtney taking on
Candice for the Heroes.
You're going for number two.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Candice not messing around at
all.
Courtney with a good slide.
Both women get to their balls
quickly.
Candice has hers.
Courtney has hers.
Got to get the ball in the hoop
now.
Candice scores for the Heroes!
Villains lead 2-1.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: All right, next
round-- Jerri taking on Amanda.
You are going to number six.
Survivors ready?
Go!
(indistinct shouting)
Amanda gets there first.
Amanda has her ball.
Jerri now has her ball.
Amanda shoots and misses for
the Heroes.
Jerri scores for the Villains!
Villains lead, three-one.
Next round.
Sandra taking on James.
You are going for number five.
Villains lead it, three-one.
We're playing to four.
If Sandra scores, Villains win
reward.
>> Come on, Sandra!
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
>> No pressure.
>> PROBST: Go!
James, no trouble, grabs the
ball, keeps going, up on his
feet like he's done it before.
Sandra crawling her way to
number five.
James scores for the Heroes!
Villains lead, three-two.
Next round, Danielle for the
Villains taking on Rupert for
the Heroes.
Villains lead it, three-two.
We are playing to four.
If Danielle scores, Villains
win.
You're going for number one.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Danielle not messing around,
launches herself.
Has her ball first.
Rupert loses his.
Rupert playing with a broken
toe.
Danielle drops her ball now.
Everybody panicking.
Big reward on the line.
Both tribes want it.
Rupert must score to keep the
Heroes in it.
>> Come on, Rupert, take your
time.
>> PROBST: Danielle can win it
for the Villains.
(frustrated shouts)
The Villains can smell that
reward.
Rupert scores for the Heroes!
We are tied, three-three.
(Rupert yells)
It's going to come down to one
last point.
Last match-up of this challenge
will be Colby for the Heroes
taking on Tyson for the
Villains.
Winner wins reward for their
tribe.
You're going for number ten.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Donaldson has his ball.
Tyson right behind.
Tyson has his ball.
Donaldson gets off the first
shot.
Just misses.
Tyson... just misses.
>> Come on, Tyson, you got it!
>> Come on, Tyson!
>> PROBST: Tyson just misses
again for the Villains.
Both guys very close.
>> You can do it!
>> Come on, Tyson!
>> PROBST: Tyson scores for the
Villains!
Villains win reward!
All right, Heroes, I got
nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Congratulations, Villains.
Come grab your reward.
>> Sears!
(whoops)
>> Good work.
>> All right!
>> Well done.
The challenge was great, and the
dragon slayer's feeling top-
notch.
I'm ready to rock and roll, and
I'm ready to move forward.
Will I change? No.
Will I be the dragon slayer
and slay everybody? Yes.
Will I wear my heart on my
sleeve every day?
Absolutely, unequivocably, yes.
>> Nice.
>> I open the tools, I grab this
serrated blade, and I notice
something in it immediately.
(indistinct chatter)
>> A little note here in this.
>> Uh-oh.
>> There you go.
>> Woops.
>> I thought that it was
something that holds the blade
in place.
I wasn't thinking.
And I'm like, man!
I just blew it!
>> "An immunity idol is hidden
at your camp, and you have
found the clue.
Head down to the beach to a
crazy palm which juts out over
the sea.
Go just beyond it and to the
right and dig around the roots
of the double tree."
>> So I grabbed the note.
Little did I know it was a
clue to a hidden immunity idol.
Who knew?
There were never any hidden
immunity idols when I played
the game.
What do you guys want to do?
We can all go find it and then
do what with it?
>> If you get it, we're going
to write your name down so that
we force you to use it.
It's not fair for one person to
have an immunity idol.
>> Rob says we're finding the
hidden immunity idol all
together and we'll get rid of
it, but they're too dumb to
walk even down the beach.
This is a bunch of idiots out
here!
Man, if I could find that
hidden immunity idol, I will
become powerful in this game.
>> Could you guys give me a
little help here?
We got to clean all of this, and
we have to make a floor.
>> Okay.
>> And then we can take a piece
of wood and push it out, so
it's more of a shelter.
>> Yep.
>> There's no way that I can
get a clue for the hidden
immunity idol and not find it.
That's not going to happen.
So I'm thinking that that's the
palm over the water, and they
have two trees right next to
it, so I'm going to find it.
>> Okay.
>> The question is, is he
really going for a walk, or is
he going looking for the idol?
>> I mean, it sucks, but that's
what we said, right?
>> That's what we said.
We said, if you go for it, then
you seal your own fate.
>> Exactly.
>> Russell's a bonehead.
He's like the hobbit on crack.
And you know what?
I don't trust Russell's ass at
all.
And the safest thing to do with
someone like that is to just get
rid of him right away.
>> Oh, me, too, by far.
Everybody slept pretty sound
last night.
You can put a little more,
maybe.
>> 'Cause it was kind of weak,
wasn't it?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Oh.
>> Hmm.
>> I wonder what this is?
>> I don't know, but hurry up
and open it.
>> Oh, "An immunity idol is
hidden at your camp...
and you have found the clue.
At the end of your beach,
you'll find the right angle.
In a clearing are three
sections of a tree.
One tall, one fallen, and one
on the ground.
Dig under the rock beneath the
90 degrees."
(Tom laughs)
Think one of us was supposed to
find this and not all of us?
(laughter)
>> For real!
>> This morning everything
changed.
As we poured out the coffee, we
found a clue to a hidden
immunity idol somewhere on our
beach.
Colby and I are on the outs
with this tribe with no way to
get in, so we need this to stay
alive in this game.
>> There went J.T.
>> Hmm.
(laughs)
>> I think I'll go this way.
>> Damn!
>> We searched the first
clearing.
I moved to the next one,
immediately saw a leaning tree,
a fallen tree, an upstanding
tree, forming a triangle.
Everybody was going to see it,
I felt, so I had to get down
and try to get it first.
James arrived.
I moved to a different spot,
'cause I could see that the sand
was a little loose.
I knew I was on it.
So I dug quickly.
And while nobody was looking,
I found the immunity idol,
dropped it into my sock.
Now, a few more people are on
the scene.
We got... Candice is over there.
It's getting a little crowded,
and I have no idea what to do
with this thing.
>> Tom, he was acting a little
funny, and when I came up on
him, I saw him put something
into his sock, and then he went
behind a tree.
So I knew he had it.
>> Like, there's a lot of rocks
under here.
>> Tom has it.
>> Aw, shucks.
>> You know, we were getting
along so good.
Now this is going to make
everybody crazy again.
>> She did? All right.
>> The hidden immunity idol
changed the whole playing
field, and that's all we needed.
We needed an opening.
Tom and I needed an opening to
get back in this game.
Granted, neither Tom nor
myself, we're not comfortable.
But we're in a little bit
better of a position than we
were a couple of days ago.
>> Yeah, right, what a morning.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Let's do it.
>> PROBST: First things first,
J.T.
Give it up.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, one
person will be strapped inside a
giant ball.
That person must then guide two
other tribe members, who will be
blindfolded, as they push the
ball down a long, winding
course to a table maze.
The person inside the ball must
then guide four other tribe
members, also blindfolded, as
they maneuver the ball through
the table maze to the finish
hole.
First tribe to finish wins
immunity, lives to see another
day.
Losers go to Tribal Council.
Somebody will be voted out.
This entire season, we've been
doing classic challenges from
past seasons of Survivor.
This challenge is classic for
another reason.
This is the only challenge in
the history of Survivor to not
be completed.
It was stopped last season due
to a medical emergency.
So although Russell has run
this challenge, one of these two
tribes will get the honor and
distinction of being the first
tribe to win it.
Villains, you're sitting out
two people in this challenge.
Who's sitting out?
>> Courtney and Sandra.
>> PROBST: Courtney and Sandra
sitting this one out.
Heroes, you're sitting out one
person.
Who's it going to be?
>> Cirie.
>> PROBST: Cirie sitting out
for the Heroes.
Sit-outs, take a spot on the
bench.
Give you a minute to strategize,
we'll get started.
All right, stepping up and
leading for the Villains is Rob.
Tom calling the shots for the
Heroes.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Doing good, doing good.
>> PROBST: Heroes off to a quick
start.
>> Keep doing what you're doing.
>> PROBST: Tom is guiding Rupert
and James.
>> You're ahead of them and
just control.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob is guiding
Coach and Tyson.
>> Together, together, together!
Together, together, together!
>> Move to push, James! Go!
>> PROBST: We're neck and neck
right now.
>> ...Tyson, now. Tyson now.
Tyson now. Tyson now.
>> PROBST: Villains now in the
lead.
>> Come on, guys, move it now,
move it now.
We're wide open, wide open.
Wide open.
(thudding)
>> PROBST: Rob takes a big hit
on that tree.
>> Together.
>> ...take the turn, hard left!
>> Keep going.
There you go. Come on!
>> That's good.
A little towards Rupert.
A little faster.
They're just a little ahead of
us.
>> A little speed.
Coach's side, Coach's side.
>> PROBST: Villains very close.
>> Right to the side.
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfolds, Coach and Tyson.
>> Okay, take 'em off, guys...
Take 'em off.
>> PROBST: Get him in a position
so he can see, and then you can
start calling shots.
>> Right there.
Okay, Parvati, down.
>> PROBST: Rob is guiding
Parvati, Russell, Danielle and
Jerri.
>> Okay, good.
>> PROBST: Heroes are now here.
>> I'm in.
>> PROBST: Take off your
blindfolds, get him oriented.
>> Get me straight.
J.T. and Amanda, down to the
left a little bit.
>> PROBST: Tom guiding Colby,
Candice, J.T. and Amanda.
>> A little more, a little more,
a little more.
Okay.
>> Danielle, slowly lift it up.
Russell down.
>> PROBST: If they're right, the
Villains have a bit of a lead.
>> I want Danielle and Russell
to come up at the same time.
Now.
Good. Don't move, don't move.
>> Colby and Candice towards my
voice now.
Towards the guys, towards the
guys.
A little more, a little more,
a little more, and a hard left.
Hard. Yes! Great!
>> There's a little gate here,
so this is going to be the
tricky part, 'cause we can't let
it go through.
Parvati up, up.
Russell, up, up, up.
Good, good.
Don't move...
>> PROBST: Rob with a big move
for the Villains.
>> All right, we want to go hard
towards the ladies.
Hard towards the ladies.
Yes! Great! Perfect!
>> PROBST: Tom with a nice move
for the Heroes.
>> Russell and Danielle, slowly
up.
Parvati up.
Okay, don't move, don't move,
don't move!
>> PROBST: Very close now for
the Villains.
>> Keep going now.
Amanda's corner down, J.T. up.
>> PROBST: Heroes close.
>> Jerri down, Jerri down.
Oh!
>> Down towards Amanda.
Oh! No!
>> Jerri, up, up, up.
And we got it.
>> We got it!
>> PROBST: Villains win
immunity!
(cheering)
>> Oh, my God!
(screaming)
>> I can't do anything.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Hey, can someone help me out?
>> Good job, Rob.
>> Good team work.
Good team work.
>> PROBST: All right, Rob, you
stepped up in a very gutsy
position as caller.
Paid off.
Immunity... for the Villains.
>> Yay!
(applause)
>> PROBST: Heroes, you have the
afternoon to figure out who's
going home.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
>> We're going back to Tribal
Council, and getting rid of
Colby or Tom tonight would be
the smart thing to do.
They have been on the outs with
our tribe since maybe day three.
And for my game, I need some of
these strong people gone.
(sighing)
>> I'm sorry, guys.
>> No, you had the hardest damn
job of it all.
>> The challenge was a
heartbreaker.
Colby and I are low men on the
totem pole within the tribe, and
the last thing I need is to be
marching off to Tribal Council
tonight.
I have the immunity idol, but
I'm still a target, because they
know it's in my possession.
So my game right now is biding
my time and, uh, looking for the
little cracks in their alliance
that we can use to save our
necks.
>> This is good, I think, for
us.
>> Mm-hmm.
Um, if we split the votes three
and three...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> ...on Tom and Colby...
>> ...and Tom plays the idol...
>> Uh-huh.
>> ...Colby goes home because
he's the one with the next most.
Okay?
If Tom doesn't play the idol,
that would force a tie between
the two of them.
Then the rest of us vote four on
one and two on the other...
>> So, let me just get this
straight-- tie-breaker.
And they can't vote at all.
>> And they can't vote at all.
>> Oh, so we're good.
>> So, if he plays the idol,
then, yeah.
>> So either way, we're good.
>> Right.
We're going to Tribal Council
tonight, and we kind of have a
plan of what we want to do.
Tom has the idol, and we need
to be extra careful right now.
But as long as we're all on the
same page, yeah, theoretically,
it should work out.
>> Yeah, but he's not going to
hurt us.
>> It just scares me because
Tom's smart, you know?
>> I'm just telling you, I
trust him a hell of a lot more
than I trust Candice.
I would love to have Tom and
his idol in alliance with me,
no doubt.
Tom and Colby are both
shoot-you-straight kind of
guys.
They look you in the eye, shake
your hand, tell you how they
feel, and you can take it to the
bank.
>> Hey, there.
>> But I'd rather have someone
like that I can count on than
Candice.
The scrambling, the running
around she's done the past
couple of days.
I don't trust her as far as I
can throw her.
>> So I'm trying to figure out
what makes sense to you and you
and James.
And Colby and I, as partners,
definitely makes more sense.
I think you have two guys who
are going to be honest, and two
guys who are going to compete
better than Cirie and Candice.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> My concern is that because
there is an immunity idol...
I wish there wasn't one, and
I'm trying to figure out how to
get that stain off of me.
>> Why don't you just give me
your word that immunity idol's
not going to be used against us
or something.
>> Oh, no, no.
I swear to God, we'll play that
thing as a committee.
If there was no idol, I'd feel
much better about this.
The idol is scaring me.
I can give it to you if one of
you wants it, and then it's your
idol.
>> With Tom having the immunity
idol, he's either a big threat,
or someone great to work with.
I'm a little leery of him,
because Tom has voted for me in
Tribal Council, but he was ready
to give us the idol, and there's
a part of him that I really do
think is honest.
>> We were just talking about
that.
>> I don't really trust Candice.
>> I like her, but she's too
scatter-brained.
>> I mean, I just want to win.
I just want the strongest team.
>> I want to win, too.
>> That's what I want, too.
I am totally trusting you here,
Tom.
>> Okay. Come here.
You know, I've been trying to
ingratiate myself with the
powers that be, and I had a
little something to bring to the
table at this point, so a
supposed new alliance was born,
but I don't believe or trust
anybody in this game, so we'll
see.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> He's, like, "Well, I don't
even want this thing.
I just want to be here.
I'll even give it to one of you
guys..."
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That is the dumbest thing.
Did he give it to you?
>> Amanda.
These are the same people that
wanted you gone desperately.
>> I know.
>> Desperately.
And now you're going to save
them?
This is so stupid.
Tom and Colby, and they're a
much bigger threat than she is.
Can you beat them?
Oh, my God!
Amanda-- I love her to death,
but she is not the sharpest tool
in the shed.
My alliance-- they're so
wishy-washy.
Like, these people, like, panic
and do crazy stuff.
Why didn't you tell me the plan
was changing?
Unbelievable! Unbelievable!
If she was so untrustworthy,
your girl right here wouldn't
be standing here now.
With this one, at least we can
keep her under control.
>> Well, no.
We haven't made up the final
decision yet, though, babe.
>> I know.
Come on.
Tom is very charismatic.
He's very athletic.
He's already won this game once
before.
Why keep someone like that in
the game?
It makes no sense. It's crazy.
>> Cirie is right.
Amanda wants to do it, but
Cirie's talking the rest out
of it.
At this point, you need to get
your idol out, get it, because I
ain't got any control any more.
Cirie's the mastermind behind
this whole deal.
>> You know what?
I thought that we had this thing
solid this afternoon.
Amanda-- after she talked to
Cirie-- she broke faith, and
this deal was off.
Cirie's the puppet master, and
she's got her arm jammed up
there, so it could be the end
of us.
>> They're going to vote three
for me, three for you.
>> There you go.
>> I've got to make a big
decision, a very big decision.
I've seen Cirie operate.
I know how she plays.
And it won't be long before she
gets rid of someone like me.
>> I think we do three and three
to keep Candice in and keep our
six strong.
Yes?
>> Yep.
>> All right.
>> And we're not going to
discuss it no more.
>> My gut's telling me to just
go with the flow, write Colby's
name down, and don't piss
everybody off, and my heart says
I'm going to keep the good guys
in the game and get rid of
Cirie, but you listen to your
heart, you get hurt out here, so
it's all up to me.
I know where everybody over here
is voting, except me.
>> PROBST: So, last time you
guys were at Tribal Council, you
voted out Steph, which seemed a
little surprising, given that
you've lost now three out of
four immunity challenges.
So, Tom, where is the philosophy
of the tribe in terms of voting
people out?
>> Stephenie was on the wrong
side of the numbers formed on
day one.
She was with the wrong group, so
she was sacrificed.
>> PROBST: So, Colby, if this
game is already about alliances,
is it inevitable that great
people are going to go home
early merely because they're on
the wrong side of the numbers?
>> It's unfortunate, but that
looks to be what's going to take
place.
>> PROBST: J.T., where is the
wisdom in having alliances this
early that cause you to vote out
somebody strong merely because
they're on the wrong side of the
numbers?
>> It's way too early to vote
out people that should get used
to beat the other tribe.
It's way too early for that, but
unfortunately all of these
people here are good and they
all have reasons why they should
be here.
>> PROBST: So then what do you
base the vote on?
>> It's pretty simple-- you got
to have people that's not going
to get scared.
They're going to stick to what
they promised you to begin with.
>> PROBST: Rupert, how about
you?
What are you basing your vote
on?
>> Trying to figure out how the
heck we can bond together in
these challenges and win.
But...
I made alliances that-- and
promises that I want to keep.
>> PROBST: So it sounds like
what you're saying with that
long pause is: "Not sure it will
be the best vote, but I will be
keeping my word."
>> That is exactly what I am
saying.
I am keeping my word.
>> PROBST: Wow.
>> I am going to stand up to
what I said.
>> PROBST: What part of that
makes sense?
Keeping your word in a game
called "Outwit, Outplay,
Outlast"?
Keeping your word because I'm an
honorable man and I want people
to see me that way?
'Cause I'm looking at a tribe
who-- you all keeping your word,
great.
All it's doing is giving you
more time with me at Tribal
Council.
>> And sitting here at Tribal
Council sucks, and I know I j...
>> PROBST: You're a part of the
reason, based on that
philosophy, Rupert.
>> I know I am.
>> PROBST: That's the most
honest and illuminating answer
we've had in any of our Tribals
together.
So, Cirie, how worried are you
tonight that you might be going
home?
>> I'm always worried, always.
>> Tom, do you believe Cirie is
worried that she's going home
tonight?
>> I believe that Cirie is not
worried that she's going home
tonight.
>> PROBST: Colby, are you
concerned you're going home?
>> Without question.
It's going to take a bold move
to save me tonight.
>> PROBST: James, how you voting
tonight?
>> We need to win.
I want gifts.
I want that food.
I want to hold the idol.
I want to do all that good
stuff, you know?
>> Are you going to base your
vote on that tonight?
>> Yes, yes, sir.
>> What you just said you
wanted?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay.
>> I want everybody to stop all
this crazy stuff and to win.
>> PROBST: What's the crazy
stuff?
>> Just the whole social thing.
The social game is a
distraction.
James don't do this stuff.
>> But, James, it's a necessity
if your name is the one on the
top of the list to go home.
>> Yes, sir, I hear you.
>> I agree, it's not fun, but
it's necessary when you're the
one faced with leaving, you
know.
>> PROBST: J.T., how concerned
are you that you're going home?
>> I don't feel like I'm going
home tonight, and a lot of
people are going to hate me for
saying it, but if I didn't trust
the people that I put my trust
in tonight, I probably would
already be gone, and I mean, I
trust these people I'm in
alliance with tonight.
>> PROBST: Well, there's a lot
of talk tonight about trust and
an equal amount of apparent
dissension, so I'm really
curious to see how the vote
plays out.
It is time to vote.
Rupert, you're up.
>> I think you're a great guy,
but hopefully it's you and not
me tonight.
>> Love you as a person, but
you're way too good at wrapping
some of these really weak minds
around your little finger.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area
immediately.
I'll read the votes.
>> Jeff.
I have something that I was
hoping not to use until this
team was able to use it against
the Villains, but evident in
camp today was I needed it to
save myself, so... I'd like to
play the immunity idol.
>> PROBST: Thank you.
The rules of Survivor state that
if somebody plays the hidden
immunity idol, then any votes
cast against them will not count
and the person with the next
highest number of votes will be
sent home.
This is, indeed, a hidden
immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Tom will not
count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Tom.
Does not count.
Tom.
Nobody still has any votes.
Colby.
That's one vote-- Colby.
Two votes-- Colby.
Cirie.
Two votes-- Colby, one vote--
Two votes-- Colby, two votes--
Cirie.
One vote left.
Fourth person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs.
Villains...
Cirie.
You need to bring me your torch.
Cirie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, I would say that qualifies
as your first blindside.
Should make for a very
interesting next few days.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I led the tribe to do some
dragon slayer chi.
Everybody went, except for
Russell.
>> PROBST: Russell hunts for the
immunity idol while Rob hunts
Russell.
>> If you go out there looking
for it, you're a marked man.
>> PROBST: Candice makes a game-
changing move.
>> I want to work with Tom and
Colby.
>> PROBST: And as the
competition gets more fierce,
another castaway goes down.
Hold up, let the docs take a
look.
>> Maybe I said too much or
stepped on J.T.'s toes, but I
couldn't just sit back and play
J.T.'s game.
I'm playing this game for myself
as well, so I couldn't do it.
I don't blame them at all.
I felt like I was gotten with
one of my moves.
You know, my hats off to them.
They got me.