>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor:
On day ten, when the Heroes
discovered a clue to the hidden
immunity idol...
>> "An immunity idol is hidden
at your camp."
>> PROBST: ...the entire tribe
scattered across the beach...
>> Who's walking down that way?
>> PROBST: ...each person
selfishly looking for the idol
alone.
Tom was the one to find it.
>> I have the immunity idol, but
I'm still a target, because they
know it's in my possession.
>> PROBST: Conversely, the
Villains agreed to stick
together and ignore the clue
entirely.
>> It's not fair for one person
to have an immunity idol.
>> PROBST: Except for Russell,
who searched for the idol but
couldn't find it.
And instead found himself on
the outs with his tribe.
>> PROBST: At the immunity
challenge, Boston Rob once again
led the Villains to victory.
Villains win immunity!
At the Heroes' camp, J.T. agreed
to vote with Cirie and the
majority of the tribe to take
out Tom.
>> I want Tom to go.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal
Council, J.T. betrayed his
alliance and voted for Cirie.
>> Jeff, I have something that I
was hoping not to use.
>> PROBST: So when Tom played
the hidden immunity idol, Cirie
was sent home.
Cirie, the tribe has spoken.
I would say that qualifies as
your first blindside.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Tonight, J.T. is a Hero.
I really believed my days were
done on the beach, but J.T. did
it.
At this point, it's all about
strategy.
They've made it very clear they
wanted me and Tom gone.
We're not gone yet.
We don't plan on going anywhere.
>> Cirie's game's always been
she stays loyal until things get
rough after the merge.
And the way things are going,
it's gonna get rough for us.
And I hope everybody realizes I
did it for the team and not for
me.
>> I'm a little pissed off right
now.
(chuckles)
I'm a lot pissed off right now.
Don't know about J.T. as much as
I did a few hours ago.
>> They think I saved them.
I didn't.
I got rid of Cirie when I had
the chance.
And I swear, I will never, never
turn on you guys. Never.
>> Really?
>> I swear. I swear, Amanda.
I would never lie to you.
I swear. You don't believe me?
I swear.
>> Okay.
J.T. can tell me everything he
wants to tell me, but I see
right through him.
In the back of my mind, I know
that he will lie and he makes
alliances like they're, you
know, yesterday's news.
I think he's made 20 alliances
already.
If he wants to play this game,
game on.
Bring it on.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> And flex every muscle.
And pull.
The key is making your mind tell
you body to flex every muscle.
I led the tribe out to the beach
this morning to do some
dragon-slayer chi; my own
special form of meditation and
movement.
Out to this side.
Move your arms like this.
It's complete body control.
If fuses everything together.
(Coach humming)
It just basically tells your
mind and your body to get on the
same page.
Keep the pressure on the fists.
And they all seemed willing
to go.
Everybody went except Russell.
>> Everybody this morning walks
out on the beach doing a little
Coach chi in a circle.
You know, all that
meditating crap.
(Coach humming)
While they meditating, getting
ready for the challenge-- I
guess that's what they were
meditating for-- I'm looking
for the hidden immunity idol.
You know, it's a very important
tool, so I'm-a get it.
I'm gonna find it.
It was right in my face.
That's what I was afraid of.
Today, everything changes.
Everything.
Rob's not in control of this
game right now.
This is my key.
This is my key right here.
And here it goes again.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Villains, getting your first
look at the new Hero tribe.
Cirie voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
All right, you guys ready to
get to today's reward challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, three members of each
tribe will battle to retrieve
balls in a pit.
Will then toss them to your
tribemates up on a platform, who
will attempt to shoot the balls
into a basket.
Each time you get a ball in the
basket, you score a point for
your tribe.
First tribe to score two points
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yes.
>> Hell, yeah.
>> PROBST: The winning tribe
will leave here and be taken to
a beautiful watering hole, and
you will enjoy a feast...
of... chocolate:
chocolate bars, chocolate cake,
>> I like cake.
>> PROBST: ...chocolate chip
cookies, chocolate milk.
(Jerri laughs)
>> That's the only thing I crave
out here.
>> PROBST: To make it a little
more enticing, I want to whet
your appetite with just a little
taste of chocolate.
>> Oh! Oh, my God!
That's kinda cool.
Oh, wow.
>> I'm watching my weight.
>> Oh, Amanda.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh, geez. Oh, geez.
>> There, Jeff.
>> Oh, geez. Oh, wow.
>> They don't want it?
>> We'll take theirs.
>> PROBST: Colby, you have a
look on your face like this is
annoying or somehow insulting.
I handed you the plate, and you
were, like, "I don't want this."
>> I'm not annoyed with you.
I'm ready to get to the
challenge.
>> PROBST: Free offer of
chocolate.
I'm just curious...
>> Don't need it. Let's go.
>> PROBST: I got the message,
brother, we'll go when
I'm ready.
>> Oh! (chuckles)
>> PROBST: Rupert, why nobody
eating chocolate on the Heroes?
What kind of message are you
sending to the Villains?
>> Hopefully, focus.
We don't care about the reward.
We just want to win the
the challenge.
>> We al, we're always focused
when it comes to a challenge.
That's why we keep winning.
(Rupert growls softly)
>> PROBST: All right, Villains,
you are sitting out
three people.
It has to be three women.
Sandra, Courtney and Parvati
sitting out for the Villains.
Heroes, you're sitting out one
one person.
It has to be a man.
>> I'll sit out.
I'll sit out.
>> PROBST: Colby gonna sit this
one out for the Heroes.
Sit-outs, take a spot
on the bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize,
we'll get started.
All right, in the pit for the
Villains, it's Danielle, Tyson
and Russell taking on Candice,
James and Tom.
Up on the platform it's Jerri,
Coach and Rob for the Villains
taking on J.T., Amanda
and Rupert.
>> Let's go, Heroes.
>> PROBST: We're playing to two.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Gotta get the ball and get it
back to your tribemates on
the platform.
Heroes have all three balls
right off the bat.
J.T. just misses.
Rupert-- nice little floater.
>> That a way, J.T., get close.
Come on, focus.
>> PROBST: Russell hanging
with James.
>>That a boy, James.
>> Ow!
>> PROBST: James takes a
hard hit.
Big battle down below.
Danielle comes up with it.
>> You all right, James?
>> Oh-oh, something's broke.
>> PROBST: Hold up.
Medical, come on in.
>> Come on, baby, you're
all right.
>> PROBST: Hold up.
Give him a little space.
Let the docs take a look.
>> Does that hurt if I do that?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm gonna bend it.
Can you bend it back?
>> It just buckled in.
>> Is that all right?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Claudia, what are you
looking for right now?
>> We're worried that he might
have pulled the lateral
collateral ligament or the
medial collateral ligament.
In which case, it looks stable
at the moment, and he's not
in pain.
He might have just sprained
a muscle.
So now we'll get him up and see
if he can walk on it.
Speaking of that, move your hand
up there.
>> I could walk it out?
Is that what you're saying?
>> Let's see what you can do.
>> This is weird.
It don't hurt.
All right, I'm good.
(James gasps)
>> Maybe not.
>> You're not gonna be able
to walk on it.
>> PROBST: Mmm...
>> He's out.
It keeps kind of popping out
inside there.
Sit down and we'll see what we
can do, but...
>> PROBST: But for this
challenge...?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Yeah, you're out.
>> Yeah, for this challenge,
he's out.
>> PROBST: Okay, all right.
>> Another tough challenge,
physical just like we wanted,
but right off the bat, James
got hurt.
I'm not sure what he's done to
his knee, but it doesn't
look good.
If James is pulled from this
game, you know, a lot of my
strategy's changed.
>> PROBST: All right, due to
James' injury, James is out of
the challenge, which means the
Heroes will be playing with five
people instead of six.
So whenever Candice and Tom are
matched up, you will be one
person short.
I'm gonna start from the top.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Right off the bat, Tom gets two
for the Heroes.
Coach just misses for the
Villains.
J.T. with a nice toss.
Just misses for the Heroes.
>> J.T.!
>> Block it!
>> PROBST: And that scores for
Amanda!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Heroes score!
Switch it up.
People in the pit are now
shooting.
People shooting are now in
the pit.
>> Nice work!
>> PROBST: We will rotate
every round.
Heroes win the first point and
lead 1-zip.
>> Let's go, Heroes. Come on.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Get that ball!
>> PROBST: Big battle!
J.T. takes down Boston Rob.
>> That a way, J.T.!
>> PROBST: Heroes come up with
two of the balls.
>> Come on, boys!
>> PROBST: Tom just misses for
the Heroes.
Candice just misses.
Tyson just short.
>> Get it, Rob.
>> PROBST: Another battle
between J. T. and Rob, Coach
and Rupert.
Rob and J.T. going at it.
J.T. not giving up
that ball.
Russell gets pulled off
the platform!
Rupert comes up with it
for the Heroes.
Another miss by the Villains.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Tom just misses.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Candice just misses.
>> Danielle, come on.
Don't hold onto the ball.
>> PROBST: Danielle just misses
for the Villains.
Villains have to score here
to stay in this.
Coach gets hit hard by J.T.
Tyson tries to lock one in, and
it works.
Whoa! Stop! Stop! Stop!
>> I did not mean to do that!
You okay?
>> Yeah, I'm fine.
He socked me.
>> Oh, like I meant to do that.
>> Whatever, dude, whatever.
>> Fine.
>> Not bleeding.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
We're tied 1-1.
>> Let's go, Heroes. Come on.
>> PROBST: Whoever gets this
point here wins a big
chocolate feast.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Big scramble for the ball.
Russell comes up with two
for the Villains.
Tom comes up with one for
the Heroes.
Boston Rob tosses one
and just misses.
Rupert can't hold onto it.
Danielle gets it to Tyson.
Tom battling for that ball.
Clears the way for Candice
to get it.
Boston Rob floats one,
but J.T. blocks it.
>> Oh! That was gonna go in!
>> PROBST: Boston Rob
blocks J.T.
J.T. now has a shot for
the Heroes.
In and out!
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Jerri scores for
the Villains!
Villains win reward!
(Villains cheering)
>> We get chocolate!
>> PROBST: All right, good
hard-fought battle once again
in Heroes vs. Villains.
Villains come up victorious.
You're leaving from here.
Grab your stuff, head out,
enjoy the afternoon.
>> Yes!
>> Chocolate, baby! Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: All right, Heroes,
I got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head
back to camp.
Except you, James.
Stick around.
We're gonna have Medical look
at that.
>> I hope for our sake that
James come back to camp because
we really need him.
To lose one of our best
competitors would be
heartbreaking.
It'd be a tragedy.
>> Him not being able to walk
makes me worried straight away
that he stretched it quite
significantly.
Basically, we want to keep him
in the game, but I'm afraid
that he's done severe enough
damage to take him out.
>> PROBST: All right, you're
gonna splint him up, and then
see if he can walk on it.
That's the test.
>> That's correct.
That's correct.
(all clamoring)
>> Oh, my God.)
>> I know. Where to start?
(Jerri shrieks)
>> Congratulations, guys.
We all got it, everybody.
>> Good job.
>> I need a plate.
>> So proud of you guys.
>> It's nice winning rewards.
We got two good things happening
at one time: we got rid of the
big boy James, maybe, and we got
to eat chocolates.
>> Oh, my God, I knew this was
gonna happen.
>> What?
>> Chocolate headache.
>> I have never eaten so much
chocolate in one sitting in my
entire life.
Okay, I must agree,
this is obscene.
I'm, like, in a mix of
chocolate euphoria and sickness.
(chuckles ruefully)
>> Whoo!
(woman laughs)
>> Cool, huh?
>> Yeah.
>> Lookit, we're, like, under
the ground right now.
(Jerri laughs)
So in the middle of the grounds,
there's this huge hole in the
earth, and it's about 40 feet
from the top to the bottom of
this cave, and it's full of
cold saltwater that comes in
right off the ocean.
I mean, it's like something I'd
never seen before.
>> Who's left up there with
Parvati?
>> We're gonna look real dumb
if, like, he's out here playing
us all.
>> He got it right away.
>> I guarantee it.
>> When I played Survivor,
there were no hidden immunity
idols then.
So this is all new to me.
I'm just trying to adjust as
I go along.
But at the end of the day, we
have to flush it out.
The only way to do that is
to vote for him.
>> Look, things are changing...
>> What?
(laughs)
Cheers. (laughs)
Russell having the idol puts me
in a better position
in the game.
Give me a little stronger
footing because right now
everyone's still trying to vote
me out.
The all think I'm the biggest
threat.
For some reason, I'm like some
evil mastermind who is gonna
screw all of them over, so they
all want to vote me out now.
So Russell having the idol is
definitely like a good.
He's a great ally for me.
>> Just grab onto my coattails,
girl.
Yes, you do.
>> I don't.
>> You'll ride these.
You gonna be okay.
Nobody can know this, but
somebody has to know with me
so we can work it.
I'm gonna show Coach.
I'm gonna say...
>> He's scared.
>> Yeah.
Hit him blindside, and get
rid of Rob.
>> Yay! (laughs)
>> I'm gonna have to convince
Coach to come to my side so we
can get numbers here.
I have a powerful tool and that
is the hidden immunity idol.
I have the idol.
And now we have the idol.
So we get to the merge, we have
to be to get to the merge.
We can blindside whoever we want
at anytime we want.
And let me tell you something.
on my life, that's the way
I play to keep my numbers to get
further in the game.
I don't have any problem to give
it to you to get further in the
game with the votes.
>> Wow! I mean, this is crazy.
>> Dude, it took me three
three days...
>> Whew!
>> ...and digging and digging
and digging
>> I do want to play the game
with Boston Rob, but for Russell
to trust me with that, is
huge on his part because I'm
the kind of person that if you
give me your loyalty, it's
almost impossible for me to
betray that trust.
I feel like I need to do
something monumental like
Knights of the Roundtable.
We go like this, and we put...
>> Can I do this?
>> No, you do, you would, like,
knight me just like that.
I feel like this is...
(Russell laughs)
No, I'm serious.
I feel like this is a
monumental moment...
>> Dude, it is...
>> ...and I honor you for
trusting me.
>> I would never come to you and
told you if I didn't trust you.
Coach bows down to me.
He was the one kneeling to me,
and I knight him as the king
that I am.
I knight the dragon slayer to be
part of my kingdom.
The king and the dragon slayer.
(both laugh)
>> Wow, man, that just blows
my mind, dude.
>> I have the dragon slayer on
my side now.
Then we'll weed out little
Rob's group.
It's personal with me and Rob.
I don't think he knows who he's
dealing with.
He thinks he's tough?
All right, may the best man win.
Let's do this.
>> I'm just so frustrated,
Candice, I really am.
>> I'm very frustrated myself.
>> I can't believe we, I can't
believe what happened today.
I really can't.
If he gets taken out, this will
be the second time he's been
taken out for an injury.
>> I know.
>> It's so sad.
Uh! I'm just so frustrated,
you know?
It's a reward challenge for
chocolate, and James gets hurt
hurt again.
And he could have a serious
injury.
Like, his knee, did you see it?
It was like...
>> It's just a ligament,
I think.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
James wants to be here so bad.
And he looks out for me.
(voice breaking): I'm like his
little sister.
And so it's like, I don't know.
It's just hard.
I was trying to, like, make
myself think, "Okay, if James
doesn't come back, what am I
gonna do?"
And I can't even think
about it right now.
I just hope that tonight I see
him walk down that beach.
I really do.
>> I don't think James is coming
coming back.
>> Yes, James has been gone
way too long.
If he was coming back, they
would have braced his knee, and
they would have sent him home.
>> James and I have our
differences, and, uh, I'm not
rooting against a teammate, but
in the game of Survivor,
somebody else being hobbled, in
some ways, is your advantage.
>> I mean, that's it.
Something that could affect him
the rest of his life.
>> Heartbreaking.
>> It's James.
>> James is coming back?
>> Oh, my God!
>> And he's walking!
>> I can't help it!
I'm sorry!
You okay?
>> Yeah, I'm all right.
>> James is back, and I was
so happy.
(sobs)
>> Yay! (laughs)
Oh,yay!
>> Welcome back, big man.
>> Yay.
>> Ah, yay!
>> So, yeah, what's the verdict?
>> They don't know what's wrong
with it.
I don't know.
>> Really?
>> What do you mean, they don't
know what's wrong with it?
>> 'Cause they don't know
what's wrong with it.
It's just not working.
It felt good coming back
in the camp.
I mean, we'll see how
things go.
Hopefully, my alliance will
stick together and keep me
around till my knee heals up.
I have to work with what I got
and make it happen.
Make some lemonade out of this
lemon knee.
It's crazy 'cause it don't hurt.
I'm just annoyed now, but...
>> It's not broken?
>> No.
>> It's not life-threatening.
It's just not stable, right?
>> Yeah. There's nothing wrong
with it.
Just, I just can't walk.
>> And in order to get an MRI,
what would you have
to do, leave?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, wow.
>> I don't think that's gonna be
too much of a problem.
>> You just want to be
left alone.
>> Yes. Thank you.
>> You're welcome.
>> If we lose the next immunity
challenge, there's no question
in my mind that James has
got to go.
There shouldn't be a question in
anybody's mind.
I mean, you can't lug around
dead weight.
And James is a lot of
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
So, Coach, I'm guessing there
was a lot of curiosity as to
whether or not James was still
in the game.
>> I'm glad, for one, that he's
still in the game because you
never want to see a worthy
competitor fall out like that.
So I'm very happy to see him.
>> PROBST: You guys ready to get
to your next immunity challenge?
> Yes.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: First things first:
Sandra, I know you don't want
to give it up.
(Sandra chuckles)
Once again, immunity is back
up for grabs.
For today's challenge, one
person will be your caller.
The other tribe members will be
blindfolded and paired up.
Using only verbal commands, the
caller must direct their other
tribe members to collect ten
very large puzzle pieces
scattered in the field.
Once you have all your pieces,
take off your blindfolds, and
the entire tribe works
together'
to solve the puzzle.
First tribe to get it right wins
immunity, is safe once again
from Tribal Council.
Losers, voting somebody out.
We have people on both tribes
who played this challenge
before.
Colby and Rupert for the Heroes.
For the Villains, Jerri,
Boston Rob.
Villains, you're sitting two
people out.
Cannot sit out the same people
in back-to-back challenges.
Who are the two that are sitting
out this time?
>> Me and Danielle.
>> PROBST: Tyson, Danielle, take
a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize,
we'll get started.
All right, the caller for the
Villain tribe is Jerri.
Calling for the Heroes, James.
James, I'm guessing that's
because of the limited mobility.
>> You could say that.
>> PROBST: Not a role we're used
to seeing James in.
Here we go for immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
>> Rob, you got a straight shot.
>> All right, J.T., just walk
straight.
J.T., go straight.
Tom to the left.
>> PROBST: J.T. bangs into a
barrel.
Colby and Tom bang into a
A few obstacles on this course.
>> Rupert, stop! Rupert, stop!
Stop, Rupert!
>> Stop, Coach!
Reach right in front of you.
That's a piece!
>> Where are you, J.T.?
>> Right here trying to pick
this piece up.
>> Okay, okay.
>> Rob, that is the wrong piece!
You want the one behind you.
>> That's the wrong end.
>> What do you need?
>> Amanda, you beside me?
Come here, Amanda. That's you?
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Amanda now finds her
right partner.
J.T. and Amanda heading back
with their first piece.
Russell and Parvati have a piece
for the Villains.
Rob and Courtney have their
first piece.
>> Got it?
>> Yep.
>> BOTH: Oop, sorry.
>> Rupert, step over to
your right.
There you go.
>> James!
>> No, Tom...
>> PROBST: Colby and Tom now
have another puzzle piece for
the Heroes.
Everybody heading back with
puzzle pieces.
Both callers doing a good job
right off the bat.
>> You're good, Rob.
>> Well done.
>> You dropped it.
>> PROBST: Both tribes have
three pieces back.
>> J.T., stop! No!
>> Rob, the piece on your left
is red.
Rob, the piece on your
right's...
No, not that one!
To your right.
> Not that way, not that way!
J.T., no! J.T. behind you!
>> James, this the right piece?
James?!
>> That's it.
Rupert, you got it.
>> Straight back to my voice.
>> Ah!
>> Okay, Russell, that is
our piece.
>> I don't want to trip.
>> PROBST: Two more pieces for
the Villains.
>> PROBST: That's five.
Heroes still at three.
>> Head back out.
All right, Rob, keep it...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Rupert and Candice
back with another puzzle piece.
Tom and Colby back with
the Heroes' fifth piece.
>> That's it. Stop, y'all.
>> To your right, Rob.
>> PROBST: Rob and Courtney have
another piece for the Villains.
Villains now with six pieces.
The Heroes with five.
>> James!
>> Stop! Everybody shut up
and stop!
To your left, J.T.!
>> I got it.
>> There you go.
Rupert, back up one step.
>> Stop! Walk straight!
>> Back up.
That's not a backup. Back up.
>> PROBST: Villains now with
their seventh puzzle piece.
J.T. and Amanda with the sixth
piece for the Heroes.
>> The right is open. Straight!
>> Throw it over. Throw it over.
>> PROBST: Villains now with
eight puzzle pieces.
Tom and Colby with another piece
for the Heroes, their seventh.
>> Rob, keep going straight.
Keep going straight.
>> PROBST: Rupert and Candice
with the eighth piece for
the Heroes.
We are tied up!
Each tribe has two puzzle
pieces left.
>> Tom, walk straight
right there.
(Rob groans)
>> Get it, Rob!
Come towards me! Back up!
Straight back! Straight back!
>> PROBST: These pieces are
heavy.
>> Walk straight, Tom.
Walk straight!
Rupert, to your right!
Walk straight! Walk straight!
>> PROBST: James trying to
get Rupert and Candice to find
their last piece.
>> Walk straight! Walk straight!
Walk straight!
>> PROBST: Heroes now with
nine pieces.
Villains now with their
ninth piece!
Both tribes have one puzzle
piece left!
>> Walk forward! Walk forward!
Turn around!
Stop, Rupert, stop!
Right there! Feel down
right there!
>> Coach, stop!
Coach, turn clockwise!
Everybody else go straight!
>> Candice, turn around.
That's it.
>> PROBST: Rupert and Candice
have found it for the Heroes!
>> Walk your ass!
Walk it! Walk it!
>> Come on, Rupert!
>> Bring it back! Bring it back!
Y'all gotta move! Walk it back!
Walk it back!
>> PROBST: Villains are now
behind in this challenge.
>> Walk it back!
Walk, both of you! Walk it back!
>> There's a piece right in
front of you!
That's our piece!
>> PROBST: Coach and Sandra have
the last puzzle piece for
the Villains.
>> Got it!
>> PROBST: Rupert and Candice
are back!
Take off your blindfolds!
Heroes now with a big lead
on assembling this puzzle.
>> We have the unlined
one over here.
This is the bottom with
the sand.
>> Come back to me!
> Oh, I'm tangled in the weeds.
>> We're good. We're good.
>> How about this right there?
>> That's not right.
That's not right.
>> Spin it around.
>> No, that's not right.
>> It's not right.
>> PROBST: Coach and Sandra
moving as fast as they can with
that final puzzle piece for
the Villains.
>> Towards me! Towards me!
>> PROBST: Heroes taking
advantage of that time that
James gave 'em.
>> James, I got it, man.
>> This one goes...
>> PROBST: Villains are back
with their final piece!
Blindfolds off!
Start working on the puzzle!
>> Good job, Russell.
>> PROBST: The Villains have had
great success with challenges
involving puzzles.
>> How about this right there?
>> No, no, no, no, no, it needs
a tree, it needs a tree.
Take if off.
>> Come on, guys, move it!
>> Move.
>> Work together.
>> J.T., is this over for that
size?
J.T., this one?
>> This goes on the corner.
>> That's the one I said went
on the corner!
>> Come on. Get it. Pick it up.
>> Hey, guys, come on.
Work as a team.
>> Go over there. That corner.
>> They told me "No."
>> Slide it to me.
>> I see it.
>> PROBST: Villains making up
a lot of time on their puzzle.
>> That goes like that,
Coach, 100%.
>> Yep.
>> PROBST: Heroes do not want to
go back to Tribal Council.
They are down two members in
this game already.
>> No, no.
>> No!
>> No! No, you guys, listen!
>> I see it, I see it.
>> Stop, stop, stop.
>> Calm down. Calm down.
>> Sorry, sorry.
>> PROBST: Now the Villains are
very close.
It's now the Heroes that are
in trouble.
>> No, no, no! I want...
Coach is, Coach is there.
>> That's right.
>> PROBST: Rob up on top calling
the shots.
>> Let's move it.
>> Okay.
>> Slide it in there.
>> There it goes.
>> PROBST: Rob jumps down on the
final piece!
Villains win immunity!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Nobody going home, y'all.
>> PROBST: Villains,
congratulations.
Villains have now won four out
of five immunity challenges.
Well, another good effort by
the Heroes, but the same result:
another trip to Tribal Council.
Grab your stuff, head back
to camp.
I will see you at Tribal
tonight.
Villains, enjoy the night off.
Congratulations.
Grab your stuff, head back
to camp.
>> I got 'em to where they need
to go.
We were in the lead.
Me injured is already proven
to be better than Tom.
He really hasn't done anything
in challenges but cause
confusion at the puzzle area.
I mean, what's his excuses?
He has good knees.
He's still messed up.
>> All right, so it's been
established that they can beat
us in puzzles.
I think that's fairly well
established.
>> We just can't pull it
together on the puzzles.
>> Or baskets, shooting.
>> Or pretty much anything
except sumo wrestling.
>> Pretty much.
>> God!
>> Now the conniving starts.
>> Yep.
>> What do you think?
>> James.
>> Is that consensus or do you
think that?
>> I think J.T. will go along
with it, too.
>> We're not changing,
are we? Tom?
Good.
>> Tom. Done.
>> No matter, no matter what's
wrong with James' leg.
>> James' leg; he's still
stronger than Tom.
>> All right, good.
>> Tom.
>> Why? I feel like this is
the dumbest move.
He can't run!
I mean, are we being stupid?
>> I can't run.
If that's the criteria, then
you should have put me out.
>> I feel like this is like a
really risky move.
>> Maybe.
Let's just think about it hard.
Decide together.
>> Yeah.
>> We got the afternoon to think
about it.
We need to think about it.
>> Yeah.
>> How you feeling, man?
>> Dude, I'm good.
>> I know you are.
>> This is a big-ass
distraction.
Like someone that, you know...
>> You sure?
>> Yeah, I just don't want
to go.
>> I know you're good.
>> Cool deal.
Y'all figure it out, but I
really don't want to go.
>> Logically, I should vote
out James tonight.
But if I were to try anything
snakey again, I'm around Rupert,
James and Amanda.
That would put myself in a,
in a bad spot.
>> Candice is pushing hard
for James.
If we're going totally on
strength, Candice's butt
is the weakest.
We vote Candice's butt out.
>> Yep.
>> I still, I still say Tom, but
I would, I would vote for
Candice now, too.
>> I say Tom first,
then Candice.
We're not getting rid of James.
James is okay, right?
>> No. I don't know.
>> It's just more logical to do,
to vote James out.
>> That's the way the cookie
crumbles, you know what I mean?
James is the one
that's injured.
>> I know.
We're in control right now,
you and I because we can go
either way.
Tilt the thing either way.
>> God, I hope J.T. votes good.
>> J.T. cannot cross us.
>> This is so stupid because
J.T. didn't vote with us last
Tribal Council, but I'm really
depending on his vote tonight.
'Cause if he doesn't vote with
us, that means he's voting with
Tom, Colby and Candice
against James.
>> It makes perfect sense to get
rid of James.
I mean, there's no logic
in voting to keep James and
getting rid of you.
You don't even have to plead
your story.
>> Mm-mm.
>> I'm happy to hear that
from both of you.
>> In order for us to win,
that's the best move for
us to make.
>> Yeah.
I've got another noose around
my neck, and, uh, until the
votes come up and you read
your name four times, you're
still alive in this game.
I need J.T. and Candice to see
the logic in sticking with Colby
and I and eliminating
James tonight.
I'm pretty sure Candice is
with us.
And I'm hoping that J.T. sees
the light.
>> J.T....
>> I was thinking your way.
>> I would hope so.
>> I'm voting the same as you do
then.
>> Which do we want,
Tom or Candice?
Okay?
>> All right
>> You and me.
>> I'm with you.
>> Okay.
>> Um, J.T.'s the one.
He's the swing.
I'm sure he's with us.
>> Where's J., where's J.T. on
all this?
>> J.T. says that he's with us.
>> Yep.
>> J.T. looked me in the eye
and swore he's writing Tom's
name down.
>> What's the word?
>> I guess we get rid of James.
It should be James.
>> I think tonight James should
be the one.
>> Makes all the logical sense
to get rid of James.
>> We're going to another Tribal
Council and most everybody's
looking to J.T. for a vote.
And the reason for that is
because J. T. is so wishy-washy.
J.T. flip-flops at every
opportunity that he has, you
know, because he's clearly just
playing the hand that suits
him today.
>> I swear.
>> I don't know what he's
telling everybody else, but if
he's making deals with everyone
in this posse, I can guarantee
that will come back to bite him.
>> PROBST: Let's start by going
back to the reward challenge.
James, what happened?
>> I don't know really
what happened.
I popped it, and I thought I was
okay, and I tried to stand up.
And it doesn't hurt.
It just, right now it's
not listening.
>> PROBST: Rupert, this is an
unusual situation; to have
somebody that's still in the
game, but they're immobilized.
My niece could beat James
in a race right now.
>> No, she couldn't.
>> PROBST: I watched you
walking today.
>> With this brace, yes, it's
a little bit harder.
But you couldn't beat me
in a race, man.
(Probst chuckles)
Real talk.
>> James still has some strength
in there, you know.
I want to believe that James is
gonna be okay.
>> PROBST: J.T., you can
certainly understand why if
you're James, you want to put
your best foot forward and say,
"Don't get rid of me
'cause of this."
>> Yeah, man, I understand
exactly what he's saying.
I mean there's no way I would
ever say vote me out due
to an injury.
I don't care if I had a cast
and my leg was broke.
>> PROBST: What's the level of
concern, though his spirit may
be there, physically may not be
able to perform like he needs
to be able to?
>> That's a huge concern.
I mean, a very high level
of concern.
I mean, we gotta win.
Our back's against the wall.
We cannot lose anymore.
>> PROBST: James, what do you
think happened today?
You got 'em there ahead
of the other group.
What happened during the puzzle?
We started off all right in the
beginning, and after that,
everybody just went haywire and
did their own thing.
Over here it just, everybody
went willy-nilly and tried to
solve the puzzle on each side.
>> PROBST: You keep looking
this way.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Who you looking at?
>> Them two.
>> PROBST: Tom and?
>> Candice.
>> No, he's mad because we're
thinking about whether
it makes sense to keep him
with the bum knee or not,
and that's what he's
talking about.
>> Baby, you just hustling
for your next thing.
I'm tired of arguing with y'all.
I'm honestly over both
of y'all.
It's whatever.
>> Jeff, all this pretense
about whether or not it's his
physical condition, and Rupert
saying, "Well, we think that
he's gonna be okay,"
it's all nonsense.
He's not being kept
for any physical ability.
He's being kept because
he's a loyal vote.
>> Well, it looks like Tom's
pointing the blame, but also...
>> That's the, that's the,
that's the main thing.
There's blame on us.
>> ...he tried to vote me out.
And I don't think I'm a weak
player in this game, so
it's vice versa.
>> PROBST: So, Tom, fingers
being pointed at you as one of
the people who won't shut up
and just do.
>> I don't see that.
Not during the challenges.
I don't think it plays
out that way.
Um, when he talks about
shutting up and doing what
you're told, that's his voting
strategy.
Somebody tells him, "Shut up.
"Just vote the way I'm
telling you."
It's not his game strategy.
If he's quiet during the
challenge, it's probably because
he doesn't know what's going on.
>> PROBST: J.T., is that
a fair comment?
James saying, "Tom just needs
"to shut up.
It's causing us to lose."
>> I wouldn't say that it's
causing us to lose, no.
I don't think it's right to
point the blame at nobody for us
losing 'cause none of can win.
>> PROBST: Tom, last Tribal
Council you played the hidden
immunity idol.
Clearly you felt you were in
trouble, and you were.
You got votes.
Concerned again that it's you?
>> Absolutely.
Yeah, it's me tonight unless a
couple of good people vote for
the team and for our strength
and for our unity, and not for
the numbers.
You know if somebody here thinks
that James with a busted knee is
gonna do more in the
competitions than I am, I don't
think they're being sincere.
I think they're just voting
and keeping their
numbers together.
>> If y'all really think that
guy can outperform me,
vote for me.
Put me out.
I want y'all to win.
And if y'all really think y'all
could win with him, ball,
go ahead.
But we still gonna be cool.
>> PROBST: Well, James laid it
out pretty clearly.
It is time to vote.
Colby, you're up.
>> James-- all mass, no class.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally
the votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Tom.
Tom. Two votes Tom.
James.
That's two votes Tom,
two votes James.
Tom. That's three votes Tom,
The fifth person voted out
of Survivor: Heroes vs.
Villains: Tom.
That's four. It's enough.
You need to bring me
your torch.
>> Be safe out there, guys.
>> PROBST: Tom, the tribe
has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, it's clear with tonight's
vote that even with a bad leg,
James is still more valuable to
this tribe than Tom.
That decision will certainly
be put to the test very soon.
Grab your torches, head
back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> Gather around. Gather around.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> It's Russell.
>> PROBST: Boston Rob becomes
Russell's judge, jury
and executioner.
>> He's not playing with
the amateurs anymore.
>> PROBST: But Russell has
other ideas.
>> I don't care how strong he
is, I don't care who he is.
He's threatening Russell Hantz.
When you do that, you go.
>> Watch your back, man.
>> Same thing for you, man.
>> Bitterly disappointed to be
here and not still in the game.
Wish I was fighting it out to
the bitter end with these
people, but I got on the wrong
side of the numbers early, and
just in spite of my best
intentions, just couldn't get
that turned around.
I don't think that James is up
to snuff, and I hope they're
that gonna be thinking, "Geez,
we could have used Tom."
But good luck to everybody in
it, and glad to have been here.