>> JEFF PROBST: In a totally
unpredictable season...
only one thing was certain.
>> He's threatening Russell
Hantz.
When you do that, you go.
>> PROBST: Anyone who targeted
Russell...
>> Watch your back, man.
>> Same thing for you, man.
>> PROBST: ...found themselves
blindsided instead.
Tyson, Boston Rob, Coach,
Courtney.
The tribe has spoken.
He achieved his goals with lies
and deception.
>> This is where I stand.
Hook, line, and sinker.
>> PROBST: The only person to
cross Russell and still
survive...
>> Yeah, I trust you.
>> PROBST: ...was Sandra.
>> But whatever Russell says,
he's lying.
>> PROBST: Behind his back, she
convinced the Heroes to join
forces with her and take him
out.
>> You want Russell gone?
>> Yeah.
>> Russell's gone.
>> PROBST: But Candice saw an
opportunity to further her own
game and joined up with Russell,
warning him he was in trouble.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: With her plans
betrayed, Sandra was forced to
rejoin the Villains.
>> You're saying you're going to
vote for me?
>> No, nobody's going to vote
for you.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council, a
frightened Russell played the
hidden immunity idol.
>> Russell's super-paranoid, and
that is going to be his
downfall.
>> PROBST: Russell wasted his
idol because both Candice and
Sandra voted with the
Villains...
Amanda, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving the Heroes in their
toughest position so far.
What they don't know is that
tonight, there will be two
immunity challenges, two Tribal
Councils, and two more survivors
will meet their fate.
>> Tribal Council is
interesting.
Candice-- she helped us out, in
that one vote, gets some
numbers, and now she's a threat.
Someone who flips over that
quickly to our side will just as
easily flip-flop back, so we
don't really need her anymore.
>> Candice was a pitiful player,
and she just proved it to me
tonight.
She deserved to be on the
Villains' tribe.
Colby and I are standing out on
a sinking ship now.
There are no other Heroes.
(bird squawking)
(squeaking)
>> It's going to be fun from
now on.
>> Nah. Just-Just Rupert and
Colby's not talking to me.
>> Oh. Oh...
>> Their feelings are hurt.
I mean, what game do they think
they're playing?
You know what I mean?
>> I think Russell is a
deceitful person, and anything
he says is a lie.
He could be worse than Jonny
Fairplay.
He is.
With all that building up
inside of me, I have to say
something this morning to
Russell.
My only hope is to show the
Villains that disgusting side
and ask them, truly, do they
want to be involved in that?
I'll tell you what, man.
You've already proven yourself
to be a disgusting, terrible
human being to swear on your
kids' life.
>> Well, you know what, Rupe?
It is the game, and you really
... for yourself.
>> If you want to swear on your
kids' life and call it the game,
that's fine.
I've played the game twice.
People see, I'm not that liar.
>> Do you think I care about how
I ... look to you as a man?
>> I think you don't give a damn
about anything but yourself.
>> I don't give a ... about you
or your family.
>> I know. I don't think you
give a damn about anybody but
yourself, and your team should
know that.
>> Rupert, I'm a villain.
I'm here so I just can make your
life hell.
The great powerful Rupert, the
good guy.
>> You know, you can say...
>> The second coming of Christ--
Rupert.
>> You can say whatever you
want, because it doesn't really
matter anymore.
(Russell laughs)
>> You're such a dumb ass,
Rupert.
I don't want Rupert here because
Rupert's sitting there, trying
to stir up stuff, trying to make
me mad.
I'm just telling him, "Pack
your stuff, partner.
Pack your stuff.
Get your tie-dye ready 'cause
you're going home."
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Guys ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Today, you are not
playing for reward.
You're playing for immunity.
One of you going home tonight
at Tribal Council.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: First things first,
Jerri.
You know I got to take it back.
>> It was fun while it lasted.
>> PROBST: Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
be standing barefoot on a small
wooden perch with your arm
raised about your head.
Your hand will be tethered to a
bucket.
When your hand drops, the bucket
tips, you're out of the
challenge.
Last person left standing wins
immunity.
To make it interesting, I will
tempt you by offering you food
items.
One other thing-- a twist which
will be revealed at the end of
this challenge.
Take your positions.
We'll get started.
All right, this challenge is
underway.
Rupert competed in a variation
of this challenge.
Lasted a couple of hours.
Parvati won this challenge in
Fans vs. Favorites, lasting
over six hours.
But there's one difference-- the
perch you're on today is a new
addition.
It makes it a little tougher.
All right, are you guys ready to
be tempted?
>> I want it, Jeff.
>> PROBST: You want out?
You don't even know what it is.
>> I don't care.
Whatever it is, I want it.
>> I want it, too, Jeff.
>> PROBST: So, wait.
Sandra and Russell, you both
want it without seeing?
>> Yup.
>> Yeah, I don't care what it
is.
>> PROBST: Step down then.
>> For real?
>> PROBST: Step down.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Sandra and Russell,
one minute into a challenge on
day 31, with immunity on the
line, voluntarily step out of
the challenge for an unknown
item.
>> I don't care.
>> PROBST: Here's what you're
sharing.
>> Yes!
>> Oh, my God.
>> What is it?
>> PROBST: Cookies and milk.
Oatmeal raisin, chocolate chip.
>> Oh, my God!
>> Oh!
Oh, these cookies are off the
hook.
You guys don't know what you're
missing.
>> PROBST: Down to six, just
like that.
>> Uh-oh.
He's back.
>> PROBST: Next item.
>> Donuts!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Four donuts and an
iced coffee.
>> Damn!
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: I'll give you guys 30
seconds to think about this
before I give them to Sandra and
Russell.
>> What?
(Sandra laughs and mumbles)
>> All right, I'll take it,
Jeff.
>> PROBST: Colby wants it.
Anybody else want in?
Drop out, Donaldson.
Rise to avoid the green.
>> Oh.
>> Ninja Turtle style.
>> PROBST: All yours, brother.
>> Thanks.
>> PROBST: We are down to five
people left in this challenge.
(Jerri exhales loudly)
>> PROBST: I have another item.
Let's see if I can get somebody
else to give up immunity.
>> Oh.
>> Oh, my God.
>> What is it?
>> Peanut butter and jelly?
>> PROBST: Peanut butter and
jelly sandwiches, chips, a big
bowl of candy.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Two glass of milk.
>> Oh.
>> I think I'm gonna take this
one.
>> I want to take it.
>> I'll take it.
>> I'll wait.
>> PROBST: So Danielle, Candice
and Jerri are all coming down
to share this.
Step off.
>> Oh.
>> Your pants just came off.
>> I hate you bitches.
(laughing)
>> PROBST: Peanut butter and
jelly sandwiches, chips, big
bowl of candy, two glasses of
milk.
How is it, ladies?
>> Best sandwich I ever had.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: And just like that,
we are down to two.
Parvati on one end, Rupert on
the other.
Both fighting for immunity.
We could be here a long time.
>> PROBST: Been out here over an
hour.
>> Ooh ...
>> There he goes.
>> Damn it!
>> PROBST: Rupert drops out of
the challenge.
Parvati wins immunity.
>> Oh.
>> Girl, congratulations.
>> Good job, Parvati.
>> Good work, Rupert.
>> PROBST: What happened,
Rupert?
>> Slipped. (scoffs)
I could have made it hours.
So I go home tonight.
Done.
>> PROBST: Parvati,
congratulations.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: This challenge likes
you, and you like it.
>> Yay, Parvati.
>> I love this challenge.
>> PROBST: Parvati wins this
challenge once again.
Parvati is safe at tonight's
Tribal Council, guaranteed a
one-in-seven shot at winning
this game for the second time.
All right, guys, now to the
twist I mentioned at the start
of this challenge.
This is a clue to a hidden
immunity idol at your camp.
"All hope is not lost if you
suffer defeat.
Salvation is hidden where two
paths meet.
A burning bush throws a shadow
on top of a stone under which
lies the key to not going home."
Have a fun afternoon.
I will see you tonight at
Tribal Council.
>> At the challenge, Jeff read
a clue to the immunity idol.
So the minute we get to camp,
all of a sudden, people just
started running.
>> We're gonna have to split up.
Y'all go on that one.
>> Parvati!
>> The clue said, there'll
be a burning bush, and in the
shadow there'll be the immunity
idol.
Is this a burning bush?
>> It's red, isn't it?
>> I thought it meant, like, a
bush that's on fire.
>> There's no bush on fire.
>> What the hell's a burning
bush?
>> What is this thing?
>> A dead tree.
>> It's just a dead tree.
>> Candice and Russell start
digging where there's this big
red bush.
But across from there, there's
another big red bush, so I
start digging...
and I see it.
Let me see what it says.
I can't believe I finally found
something.
Um...
I'm nervous-- I can't read this
out here.
I don't know where to put this.
It's too big.
Oh, no, it's too bulgy.
>> You think it's on these
trails?
>> Well, I mean, these aren't
really trails, right?
>> Even though I don't have the
idol, maybe I can play like I
do.
I stuck me a rock in my pocket,
making it look a little dangly,
a little big.
This isn't my first game of
Survivor.
I'm just trying to stay in it
another day.
>> What's happening, Rupe?
Feel like we're Easter egg
huntin'.
>> Yeah.
>> I have a lot of experience
with idols.
Rupert has a big, bulky thing
in his pocket.
It's the idol wrapped up in the
paper.
Now, we have to get rid of the
idol, so how are we going to do
this?
It's easy-- we'll split the
votes tonight.
If he don't play it, he goes
home.
That's how we'll do it.
>> I don't know, I think
everybody pretty much gave up.
>> He found it.
I see it in his pocket.
I know exactly how they look.
And I know exactly how they
look in a pocket.
>> Russell swears that Rupert
found the idol.
Of course, I know that's a lie,
'cause I have the freakin'
immunity idol.
And if they think Rupert has
it, that's good for Sandra.
So I'm not going to say nothing.
>> No, we'll split the votes,
three-three.
>> Why?
>> To get the idol out of
Rupert's hands.
>> We have to flush it out.
>> Oh, right.
>> So we have to split the
votes.
>> (whispers): It's perfect.
>> Colby and Candice are both
threats in different ways.
That's why it's a hard decision.
Candice voted with us to vote
out Amanda, and I really think
she's going to stay loyal to us.
Colby's not really doing any
kind of strategizing, so I feel
like I can get him to do
whatever.
I don't know, I mean, either
way, we're rolling the dice.
>> Right now we need to be safe
and make sure that idol is out
of Rupert's hands.
>> Yeah.
>> Here's how it's gonna work.
They're going to split the
votes tonight, 'cause they
got six of them, right?
So they're going to send half
of them your way, and the other
half are either going to go
towards me or towards Candice.
>> If three of them vote for
Candice, then you and I vote
for Candice, there's five votes
for Candice.
>> And even if three of them
vote for you and you don't have
the idol, you're still safe.
>> There's still five votes for
Candice.
>> Exactly. I could be going
home tonight if it doesn't
work, but if it does, me and
you get to vote Candice out.
>> Oh, God! That would be...
>> And then we've still got a
shot.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Coach... Courtney...
J.T., and Amanda, voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
All right, Rupert, let's pick
up with the last Tribal Council.
Amanda's voted out.
You all go back to camp.
What's the fallout?
>> The fallout was, we realized
there's only two Heroes left.
There's Colby and I.
Candice jumped to the Villains'
side.
>> PROBST: Candice, you're
shaking your head.
Is that not true?
>> It was obvious that Amanda
was going to go home whether I
voted for her or not.
You know, Amanda had a target
on her back because she's a
strong, strategic player.
So it wasn't like my vote was
the nail in the coffin to send
her home.
The numbers were already there.
>> I have no respect for the
excuses.
>> It's not going to get me any
further in the game to go down
on a sinking ship.
>> Well, then that's what you
should have said, that right
there.
>> Exactly right.
>> "This is a game for a
million dollars.
This was my best play."
>> PROBST: So, Russell, as a
strategy, Candice put herself
ahead of Colby and Rupert, and
that will keep her in the game
longer.
Good move.
>> Yeah, it's her best move.
She goes to the Villains' side
at number six, and unless
you're going to give all the
Villains a million dollars,
something has to break within
the Villains-- so she could have
made a great move.
>> PROBST: So if history
repeats, now we're looking at
Rupert or Colby in trouble
tonight.
>> What am I supposed to say?
I'm going to get rid of my
Villain partners out here?
No, that ain't gonna happen.
We got two Heroes that's gonna
have to go sooner or later, and
the consensus is that Rupert
goes, so...
>> PROBST: Rupert, after the
challenge was over, I read a
clue where another idol was
hidden.
You get back to camp-- what
happens?
>> We got home from our
challenge.
I calmly took my sandals off and
went for a walk in the jungle
and stayed until I felt
comfortable.
>> PROBST: So, Russell, you
think that idol's out there, or
do you think Colby or Rupert has
the idol?
>> If they don't, then they
gave up.
And I don't think Colby or
Rupert would give up.
>> PROBST: All right, let's get
to the vote.
Parvati has the immunity
necklace.
Cannot vote for Parvati.
Everybody else is fair game.
Colby, you're up.
>> I can honestly say I'm proud
of the way I played this game.
Can you?
>> My mom always told me, if you
don't have something nice to
say, don't say anything at all.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
>> PROBST: Once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Rupert.
That's two votes Rupert.
That's three votes Rupert.
Candice.
One vote Candice.
That's three votes Rupert, two
votes Candice.
Candice.
We're tied, three votes Rupert,
three votes Candice.
That's four votes Candice,
three votes Rupert, one vote
left.
13th person voted out and the
fifth member of our jury...
Candice.
You need to bring me your torch.
Candice, the tribe has spoken.
>> Thank you.
Good luck, you guys.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
Well, maybe the lesson learned
from tonight's Tribal Council is
this-- it's a risky move when
you betray trust in order to
gain trust.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> I definitely got thrown under
the bus tonight, um, but I
understand I made a risky move
yesterday, and, um, it didn't
pay off.
So I guess... karma's a bitch
sometimes.
>> Wow.
>> We just blew it.
We were supposed to split the
votes for Rupert and Colby, and
it didn't happen.
It was a terrible decision.
The girls got their heart
involved in the game, wanted
Candice out of here because
they didn't like her, so
everybody blew it.
And I'm one of them.
I should have sat them down and
said, "No, this is what we're
gonna do."
From the get-go.
...one at a...
Just Rupert alone.
>> I'm not fully in control of
this game now.
Me and Parvati are equally in
control, and that makes me a
little worried.
But you know what?
I'm going to take control of
this game so fast, they ain't
even know what hit them.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Parvati, it looks like you're
ready to give it up.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
each race to get a peg that you
will use to maneuver through a
table maze.
The first five to finish move on
to the next round, where you
will use four
individually-shaped pegs to help
you get to the top of a tall
climbing wall.
The first three to get to the
top of the wall move on to the
final round, where you must
solve a slide puzzle.
The first person to finish the
puzzle wins immunity and is
guaranteed a one-in-six shot at
winning this game and the
million-dollar check.
Losers, Tribal Council, where
after 33 days, somebody will be
sent home.
We'll draw for spots, we'll
get started.
Here we go.
First round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You've got to dig up your peg
and then get it through the
table maze.
Rupert has his, and he's off to
a fast start.
Parvati, Sandra, Danielle have
theirs.
Russell's got his.
Jerri has her peg.
Everybody on the maze but Colby.
Colby now has his peg and a lot
of time to make up.
Rupert was out very quickly.
Russell now doing a good job on
the maze.
Rupert very close.
Sandra getting close.
Rupert's through.
Rupert moving on.
Sandra moving on.
>> I can't believe it.
>> PROBST: Russell's moving on.
Parvati moving on.
One spot left.
Three people vying for it.
Jerri, Danielle and Colby.
Danielle very close.
Danielle moving on.
Moving on to the next round.
It's Rupert, Sandra, Parvati,
Danielle and Russell.
First three to the top of the
wall move on.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You have four pegs.
Use them as you want.
You don't have to use any of
them.
Russell gets himself halfway up
the wall by just running.
Rupert trying to run up the
wall.
You're going to have to run
harder than that.
Meanwhile, Parvati is moving up
the wall.
Danielle making steady progress.
Russell climbing up this wall.
Using only two pegs so far.
Russell very close to the top.
Russell to the top.
Russell's moving on.
Two more spots.
Rupert making up for lost time.
Parvati very close.
Rupert to the top.
He moves on.
Parvati to the top.
She moves on.
It is Russell, Parvati and
Rupert in the final round for
immunity.
>> Damn!
>> Now how do I get down?
>> PROBST: All right, here we
go.
The final round.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's a slide puzzle.
That means you can't pick up
the pieces.
You have to slide them around,
building that very familiar
Survivor logo.
Don't slow down.
Don't lose your concentration.
Focus on finishing this puzzle.
Russell starting to get it
together a little bit.
>> PROBST: Rupert's now starting
to come together with his
puzzle.
Parvati falling out of it.
Russell much closer now.
Rupert very close.
We are neck and neck.
>> Jeff.
>> PROBST: Russell thinks he has
it.
Russell wins immunity!
>> Way to go, Russell!
>> Good job, Russell!
>> PROBST: Russell, come on
over.
>> Good job, Russell.
>> PROBST: Russell safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
For the rest of you, after 33
hard-fought days, somebody
going home tonight.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
I'll see you at Tribal.
Congrats.
>> I was thinking as I walked
out of that darn challenge, "You
made it so far, and still came
up short."
I have to believe in myself,
because just the lie of a rock
in your pocket is not going to
save you tonight.
(thunder crackling)
>> I want Rupert to go home
tonight.
He's a Hero.
He is not part of our original
tribe of Villains.
And I'm pretty sure Rupert does
not have the idol.
So, yeah, I don't feel bad for
Rupert at all.
I think he's kind of dug his
own grave.
The Villain invasion happened,
and now the Villains are running
this place.
There ain't gonna be any Heroes
left.
No Heroes.
Seriously.
>> What do you mean locked
in...?
>> I mean, we need to be strong,
five, and get those two off,
because if those... one of those
guys makes it to the end, none
of us stand a chance.
It has to be five Villains...
>> Yeah, I know that.
>> ...and that's it.
>> I know that.
>> And honestly, right now,
we're set up pretty good,
because Rupert can go home,
Colby's not good in challenges,
and he can go home next, you
know?
>> Parvati and Danielle, to me,
they're a team, when it's
supposed to be me and Parvati.
And that's a problem.
So the only thing I can think of
right now is to break up that
couple.
>> You really think so?
>> Mm. I wouldn't take her to
the finals.
>> Oh.
>> She might try to get rid of
you or try to get rid of me.
Uh, that's going to come.
If she tries to get rid of
either of us, you know, we can
easily bounce out her.
>> Yeah.
>> Russell brought up that he
wants to get rid of Parvati, but
I don't know if we should do
that.
You know, Parvati's been my
alliance since the beginning,
and, like, if we are going to
ever do that-- which I don't
know if I am because I'm in a
tight alliance with her-- but if
we are, now is not the time.
I trust you, like, 110%.
I don't have any worries about
you.
>> Yeah, I trust you, too.
>> Danielle came to me.
She wants to vote you off when
it comes down to five or six.
>> Why would she want to do
that?
>> And I ain't messing with you,
Parvati.
You got to...
As... like I told you, my
loyalty lies with you in this
game, and that's it.
I'm working Danielle.
I'm working Parvati.
I'm telling Parvati we've got
to get rid of Danielle.
I'm telling Danielle we got
to get rid of Parvati.
So, by working both of them,
I got both of them under
control.
Parvati's not going to tell
Danielle, Danielle's not going
to tell Parvati, 'cause it'd
mess up both of their games.
>> Well, I want to talk to her.
>> Are you serious?
>> Yes, I'm serious.
>> About what?
>> You can't just come at me and
tell me that my final three from
day one wants me out.
>> Oh, my God.
>> And you think I'm not going
to talk to her?
>> You gonna talk to her?
>> I'm not going to tell her you
told me that, but...
>> She's going to know...
>> ...I'm gonna find out what
she's saying.
>> Parvati, if you do that,
you're out of this game.
I promise you.
Are you serious?
You're going to go tell her
exactly what I'm trying to keep
a secret from her?
>> I just told you, I'm not
going to say what you're saying.
>> You can't even bring it up.
Go ahead.
Do what you think you need to
do, Parvati.
>> Don't yell at me, Russell.
>> I can't believe you're,
you're thinking like this.
>> Thinking like what?
Like I want to have a ...
conversation with someone?
>> You can't go up to her and
say anything...
>> Don't tell me I can't have a
conversation with someone.
>> Okay, all right.
You go talk to her.
You do that.
>> Today should have been
Rupert: done.
Russell comes out of nowhere
and says, "They're blind-siding
"you.
That's what's happening."
I'm, like, "I'm not voting
"Danielle tonight.
"I don't care what you say.
I'm not doing it."
>> It could be dangerous if
Parvati would talk to Danielle
about what I told her that
Danielle wants to get rid
of Parvati.
It could turn into a problem.
>> She wanted to blind-side you!
>> He said that to you?
>> Yes.
>> He told me that you came up
to him and said that you wanted
to blind-side me now
because, um, you don't think you
can win against me and, like,
all this other stuff.
>> He's such a liar.
>> But I'm not voting you
tonight.
I won't. I refuse.
>> So Russell's trying to vote
me out tonight?
>> We have to get out Rupert
or Colby.
>> I know.
He's got this whole thing, like,
he wants me and you to be, like,
at each other's throats...
>> I think he's worried that if
it's at the final three and it's
you, me, and him...
>> He's gonna...
>> ...you and I will take each
other, and he'll be out.
>> I'm-a get Danielle off
tonight because it
eliminates that pair.
As soon as we get rid of
Danielle, Parvati is going to
be so scared of me, she's gonna
stick to me like glue.
And she's gonna vote the way
I tell her to vote.
There's only one thing that
has to happen today, and that's
Danielle go home.
>> Really?
Really?
>> Yeah.
>> It's funny how things change
in this game.
>> I know, I know, damn it.
>> How did this get flipped
on me?
>> It's crazy.
>> Why? Why do we want to keep
Colby and Rupert around?
That doesn't even make
any sense.
>> It doesn't make sense.
It does not make sense.
>> Russell running around
double talking is hurting
his game.
He's getting outplayed by me
and Danielle at this point, and
it's making him a little
bit crazy.
The only thing we have to do is
make sure Jerri doesn't write
your name down.
>> I'm ripping my hair out.
Do not change your vote tonight,
no matter what he says to you.
>> Oh, no, I won't.
>> He's trying to vote me out.
>> He's trying to vote her out
tonight.
>> It's Rupert.
>> Insane-o.
>> Are you crazy? It's Rupert.
>> He's causing all this...
craziness again.
>> Please don't write my name
down tonight.
>> I want Danielle gone
tonight.
>> We need to get rid of Rupert.
>> Bad move.
You're going to be next.
Not 'cause of me.
>> Don't threaten me.
>> Not 'cause of me.
I'm trying to save you.
You don't get rid of Danielle,
you're gonna be after her.
>> Why do you say that?
>> It ain't me. It ain't me.
I can't do nothin'.
You have to help me help you.
>> Who are you talking about?
Explain to me why that's even...
>> I can't.
I'm telling you now, we have to
get rid of Danielle tonight, or
they will get rid of you.
>> PROBST: Now bring in the
members of our jury.
Coach... Courtney... J.T....
Amanda... and Candice, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Rupert, who's running this show
right now?
>> I don't know.
It's probably between Parvati
and Russell.
>> PROBST: Danielle, ring true
to you-- Russell and Parvati
pretty much guiding the shots
over here for the Villains?
>> Um, I don't necessarily
think that's true.
I think the Villains make
decisions together.
>> PROBST: Really?
This close to a million dollars,
you all agree?
>> Yeah, we're still together,
aren't we?
>> PROBST: That doesn't mean you
agree.
>> But we agree voting out the
Heroes and sticking together.
>> PROBST: So, Jerri, around
camp must be fairly peaceful,
then.
The Villains all agree on the
decisions, and Rupert and Colby
going, "It's you or me, dude."
>> Hell, no.
It's never been quiet since day
one playing this game, and it is
certainly not quiet right now.
>> PROBST: So, Danielle, why
this illusion that it's one big
happy family?
>> There was just a
miscommunication, Jeff,
honestly.
There were things said, and, no,
not everybody agreed today, at
all.
It was mad chaos.
>> "Crazy" could not describe
what happened today.
>> Craziness, crazy, crazy.
>> Like, unnecessarily out of
control, like...
>> Danielle and I were pitted
against each other.
>> We were pitted against each
other.
>> PROBST: Parvati, what
happened?
>> Well... Russell came to me
and told me that Danielle was
trying to blindside me today.
She said it was not true and
went crazy. (laughs)
And so Russell's trying to test
loyalty.
That's what I got from the
whole thing.
>> PROBST: So, Russell, you got
caught.
>> No, I didn't get caught doing
nothin'.
Today, Danielle came up to me
before I said anything and said,
"When do you...
>> Lies. Liar. Liar.
>> "...when do you want to get
rid of..."
Let me finish talking.
Danielle knows where my loyalty
lies, and that's with Parvati.
If you gonna come up to me...
>> And me, you've been
telling me...
>> If you gonna come up to me,
if you gonna come to me and try
to get rid of Parvati...
>> For the last...
>> ...then I'm gonna try to get
rid of you.
>> You just sat me on the beach
and said that you don't want to
go against Parvati at the end
because you think...
>> I wanted to see where you
stood, and I exactly found out.
>> Oh, really?
>> The three of us are in an
alliance, so I don't
understand why.
I haven't done anything to be
disloyal to him.
I don't understand why he's
testing me.
I don't know.
(voice breaking): Oh, my God.
(chuckles)
>> PROBST: What are the tears
about right now?
>> (sobbing): I'm just a
frigging wreck!
I'm so exhausted, and I'm just
like...
It's just too much for me
right now.
Oh, man.
I just had a rough day.
We've been in an alliance since
the beginning.
I don't know why he's trying to
mess with it.
>> PROBST: Is it feeling
personal to you?
Is that hurting your feelings?
>> Yeah!
>> I don't understand how she's
just putting it all on me.
Why I'm trying to mess with it
when she agreed totally
with that.
>> Because you were telling me
she wanted to get me off.
What am I supposed to say?
>> And when she said, "Let's
get rid of..."
Can I finish, please?
>> No.
>> Whatever.
>> You're such a liar.
It wouldn't have happened.
It didn't.
>> It would have happened if I
would have wanted it to happen.
>> It would not have happened.
I'm closer to Parvati than
you think.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah, really.
>> Okay.
>> PROBST: Boy, that perked
you up.
>> We're all fine right now.
There's no need for us to
continue with this conversation.
It's been resolved.
At least, it was resolved today.
>> PROBST: Well, it just got
reopened when you said you're
closer to Parvati than Russell
thinks.
>> No, he is underestimating,
like, my friendship and my
loyalty to her, and I don't
like that, so I'm just letting
him know that I would never do
that to her.
PROBST: All right, then let's
get to the vote.
Russell has the
immunity necklace.
You cannot vote for Russell.
Everybody else is fair game.
Danielle, you're up.
>> Okay, second time's
the charm, right?
Hopefully, you're going home
home tonight.
>> (whispers): You're closer to
Parvati than I think?
That makes me think that y'all
got something going on, so I'm
gonna have to cut that tie.
>> I have absolutely no idea
what just happened, but with
this vote, I'm sealing my fate.
>> PROBST: I'll go
tally the votes.
If anybody has the
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
All right, once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Rupert.
Two votes Rupert.
Three votes Rupert.
Danielle.
Three votes Rupert,
one vote Danielle.
Danielle.
That's three votes Rupert,
two votes Danielle.
Danielle.
We're tied.
Three votes Danielle, three
votes Rupert.
One vote left.
14th person voted out and the
sixth member of our jury:
Danielle.
You need to bring me your torch.
Danielle, the tribe has spoken.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: So here's what we
learned tonight: the Villains
are clearly not one big, happy
family.
Colby and Rupert live to see
another day, and it is
anybody's game.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
>> I'm against you, Russell.
>> PROBST: Russell is on the
outs with the Villains.
(Parvati giggles)
So he tries to turn the Heroes
to the dark side.
>> Greatest Villain, the
greatest Hero.
I want to trust you all the way
to the final three.
>> Final three. Final three.
>> Russell is insane.
And tonight, I might have put
my own foot in my mouth at
Tribal Council by basically
just calling him out in front
of everybody.
And I think he changed his vote
the last minute, actually.
I feel like I played a good
game and maybe a little too
aggressive this time.
But I did the best that I could
and that's all you can ask.