>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Villains win immunity!
>> Yes!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: For three long weeks
the Heroes had been perfecting
the art of failure.
Villains have now won four
out of five immunity challenges.
To make matters worse, Colby,
a consistent winner in seasons
past, was tangled in mediocrity.
>> He has not done anything.
It's, like, my superman sucks.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, the
Villains appeared
to be invincible.
>> I feel so... (growls).
>> You feel like a big man?
>> PROBST: But the announcement
of a double Tribal Council...
Tonight, both tribes are voting
somebody out.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: ...exposed the
villain's Achilles' heel; a rift
between Russell and Boston Rob.
I don't trust Russell's ass
at all.
He's like the hobbit on crack.
>> It's personal with me
and Rob.
I don't think he knows who he's
dealing with.
>> PROBST: Danielle and Parvati
were firmly in Russell's camp,
with Sandra, Courtney and Tyson
in Rob's.
Both sides were vying for the
attention of the dragon slayer
and his fair maiden.
But right before Tribal Council
Russell planted a seed
in Tyson's head, suggesting he
vote out Parvati.
>> I'm going to vote for
Parvati, and then that
will be it.
I don't like doing it,
but I got to.
>> Deal.
>> All right, man.
>> Yup, we're tight, dude.
>> PROBST: But at the Villains'
Tribal Council, Russell pulled
a double cross by giving
Parvati his hidden
immunity idol.
She played the idol, Tyson took
the bait, and Boston Rob's
closest ally went home.
Tyson, the tribe has spoken.
Later, when the Heroes took
their seats at Tribal Council,
Colby dodged a bullet when the
tribe voted out James because
he was injured.
Now, only five Heroes remain
against eight Villains.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> I've played Survivor
three times now, and for the
first time in all of those
times, I was shocked last night.
I completely didn't know
what happened.
The more and more I think about
it, something doesn't
feel right.
Something just doesn't feel
Let me tell you something, dude,
somebody said something to him.
>> He didn't want to tell you.
>> Who cared? That's so stupid.
>> Well, he's not here anymore,
is he?
>> It just hurts all of us.
We need to knock them out.
Danielle's dumb as a bag of
rocks anyway.
Both Parvati and Russell can do
some damage.
>> It's no secret that Russell
has a little-boy crush on
Parvati because he's...
I mean, let's face it, he's
like a bandy-legged little
troll who, you know, sort of,
like, scampers around with his
tooth missing and, you know, is
in and out of the bushes and
never washes.
And she pays attention to him,
And she has, like, no problem
flirting with clearly anything
that walks.
>> My hero! (chuckles)
>> That was awesome last night.
>> Awesome, wasn't it?
>> Y'all two need, y'all two
need just to work on Jerri.
(Parvati laughs)
Y'all two together can
do it easy.
(women giggling)
>> I don't understand how they
can be so cocky right now,
making fun of people.
How can they do that, Jerri?
There's three of them, there's
five of us.
(giggling continues)
I was born at night, but not
last night.
To me, it's ridiculous that
three people would have so much
confidence unless something else
was going on.
>> I'm so crafty. (laughs)
>> I don't know if they
were just excited because
they pulled over a big, stupid
move or if they think that
they have numbers on the other
side and the merge is coming
soon, or possibly if two of
those people that are sitting
with me in the tent pretending
to be mad at the other three
are actually with them, and the
joke's on me.
(Danielle groans)
>> What's up, girl?
>> I didn't sleep for crap, man.
>> I didn't either.
>> It was cold.
>> My blanket was halfway off
my body.
That's why I was freezing.
>> That was hard.
>> Rob started yet?
>> Started?
>> Started his ranting
and raving?
>> No, everybody's still
sleeping-- well, relatively
sleeping.
I think everybody's really
depressed.
>> I ain't depressed.
They're depressed.
>> Yeah.
>> Just think of you as on the
outs like them, you know?
Depressed like that
and going mad.
That ain't a good feeling.
>> No.
>> If you have a tight alliance
with four people, five people,
you can get all the way down
to the end if you, if you
stick together.
That's how people get
far in this game.
>> I think Jerri has all kind
of respect for me now, because
I put my butt on the line for
somebody else.
Now she has an alliance that
she has to start a relationship
with.
Jerri hated Parvati.
I brought them together.
But I'm that good where I can
bring people together in this
game for my good.
>> I'm just...
I'm afraid to commit.
I mean, I'll be honest.
I-I've had my trepidations
with you from the beginning.
>> If people are worried
about me, then, I mean, there's
just-- what can I say?
I've been, like, (laughs)
I've been the target of
every single vote because
everyone thinks I'm gonna get
with my people.
Why would I do that?
Because it doesn't make sense
for me leave a solid tribe.
>> I guess it's, maybe
I have fears of commitment.
Maybe that's why I've been
single for three years.
(laughs)
It hurts my brain.
>> Jerri's completely
noncommittal.
I thought I was noncommittal.
She's, like, "People have hurt
"my feelings in the past, and
"I've just not gotten over that
"for 38 years.
"I've been harboring resentment
"for the people that have lied
to me and hurt my feelings."
Well, listen, crazy pants,
it's like a 3-3 split right now:
It's me, Russell, and Danielle
on one side, Rob, Sandra and
Courtney on the other side,
Coach and Jerri right in
the middle, you know?
They don't know which way to go.
"Which way do we go?"
>> Isn't it proof?
The girls in Micronesia.
>> It's up to you.
I mean, like, we can't do
anything else other than
top four.
That's it.
But I think Jerri is leaning
more towards coming with us
because she saw what Russell
did for me, and I think, I
think Jerri's a little bit
jealous that a man hasn't done
that for her, so I think she
wants to take a chance for
with Russell.
Maybe he'll save her life and
she can have a hero.
(birds calling)
>> It's really cold.
>> Oh, God, my knees hurt.
Everything sucks.
Poor James, damn it.
If we ever needed somebody to
step up, we need Colby to step
up today.
Tribal Council last night, we
ended up putting James out of
our camp.
I don't know exactly if that
was the right decision or not,
but we've got to keep strong.
We cannot let the Villains
keep winning.
>> Unbelievable.
I have survived two, if not
three huge Tribal Councils
where going into them, I was
convinced I was going home,
but, uh, here I am.
>> Oh, my God, he's going to
come back with a vengeance.
>> Yeah.
>> He's got something to
prove today.
>> There's a little bit of
pressure on me to perform
'cause clearly, if James' knee
had held up, I wouldn't be here.
So now it's put up or shut up
time for Colby.
I'll do everything I can to
make you guys realize you made
the right decision.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Villains getting your first
look at the new Hero tribe.
James voted out the last
Tribal Council.
You guys ready to get to
today's reward challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, yeah!
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, three members of
each tribe will race through
the water to get a ball.
You must then work together
until you can shoot your ball
in your basket while members of
the other tribe attempt to stop
you any way they can.
Each time you get a ball in
your basket, you score a point
for your tribe.
First tribe to three
wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: The winning tribe
will leave here and be taken to
an outdoor waterfall.
You'll enjoy a nice healthy
lunch.
You'll have beef, chicken,
tuna...
>> Oh, yeah.
>> PROBST: ...fresh fruit.
Should send you back to camp
completely rejuvenated.
Villains, you have three extra
members; sitting three people
people out.
Cannot sit out the same people
in back-to-back challenges.
You have to sit out three women.
Courtney, Sandra...
>> Me.
>> PROBST: ...and Parvati.
Sit-outs take a spot on
the bench.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize.
We will start three men on
three men.
All right, here we go,
first round.
We'll have one person under the
goal, two people on the flag.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, guys!
Come on, Colby!
>> PROBST: Rupert has it for
the Heroes.
Russell can't even catch him.
Rupert waltzing in.
Rob tries to steal it for
the Villains.
J.T. now has it.
Coach takes down J.T.
Colby has it for the Heroes!
Just misses!
>> Come on, Colby.
Get it in there!
Colby, get it!
>> PROBST: Colby with another
shot!
Just misses.
>> Come on, Rob, get it!
>> PROBST: that ball's wide
open.
Rob and Colby going for it.
Big scramble for the ball.
Coach now has it for
the Villains!
Coach now with a free shot.
>> Wide open, Coach!
>> PROBST: Not even close.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Coach with the
rebound and the opportunity to
score, but he blows it.
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Colby knocks Coach
down, takes the ball, racing to
the hoop.
>> Come on, Colby!
>> PROBST: Colby scores for
the Heroes!
Heroes lead, one-zip.
Next round.
Two women from each tribe
along with one man.
Heroes lead it one-zip.
We're playing to three.
>> Let's go, girls.
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
Villains need to score.
Candice takes Danielle down,
leaving Amanda open.
Once again, Coach and Colby
matching up.
Colby has had Coach's number in
this challenge.
He eludes him again.
Colby comes up short.
Coach now for the Villains.
>> Get it, Colby!
>> Just hold him, Candice.
>> Coach, it's a chick!
Come on!
Get it to Danielle!
>> Get it, Jerri!
Get in there, Jerri!
>> Come on, Jerri!
>> PROBST: Colby now takes it
from Jerri, over to Candice.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Candice in and out
for the Heroes.
Candice misses.
Coach has it again, launches a
long shot.
Colby just tosses Jerri out of
the way.
Heroes way more aggressive in
this challenge.
Colby to a wide-open Amanda.
Danielle blocks Amanda twice.
Candice has it for the Heroes,
Candice scores for the Heroes!
Heroes lead two-zip!
>> Good work, team!
>> Yeah.
PROBST: Next round, the men are
back out.
This could be it.
Heroes lead 2-zip.
Villains have yet to get on
the board.
We are playing to three.
>> Come on, Heroes!
Finish it off right now!
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
J.T. sprinting after that ball.
Nobody even close to him.
Russell takes Rupert down.
They're going at it.
J.T. has it, passes to Colby
underneath the goal.
This challenge is over!
Heroes win reward!
>> Yeah! Yeah!
>> We won! Whoo!
>> PROBST: Villains, got
nothing for you.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
Heroes, been a while since
you've had something to
to celebrate.
>> Whoo!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff,
head out, enjoy it.
>> Thanks, Probst.
>> Have a good day, Jeff.
I know we will.
>> We dropped the hammer on the
Villains, and for me
personally, I had a lot riding
on this.
A win like this today not only
buys me a little more time but
it relieves the tension in my
in my tribe.
>> Oh, my...
>> Today just proves that we are
a family.
We're together.
We're a much stronger team than
they are right now.
We've got them on our heels, and
it's time for a little
redemption.
>> To Heroes!
>> Love you!
>> Fantastic Five!
>> Oh, look at these!
>> Yes!
>> They are.
>> Oh.
>> I'm going to have some beef.
>> I want some beef.
>> Oh!
>> If we stay together, us
five, nobody can stop us, guys.
>> Mmm.
>> You guys, there's another
immunity idol.
>> What are you reading?
>> At our beach.
>> What?
>> Do you want to just read it
later, and we'll all read it?
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> When Candice pulled that
letter out, it brought the game
back home.
Before then, we were out of the
game.
We were having a meal.
We were having a nice time as
our Fantastic Five.
>> Of course, we all tried to
ignore the clue.
We had such a good time, such a
good thing going for a few
minutes, and the game still
creeps back in.
>> Just couldn't wait, could
you, Amanda?
>> Well, if you're going to
read it, read it out loud so
everybody can hear it.
>> Yeah, give everybody the
details.
Got to read it out loud.
>> Calm down.
I was just wondering.
"Another immunity idol is
hidden at your camp.
Stroll down your beach to the
river's bed.
Atop the second bridge, you'll
see a tree rooted where two
currents meet.
Behind it, in a shallow grave,
it shall be."
>> Let's not let that come
between us.
>> Yup.
>> If y'all want, we'll go look
for it together.
That is for us to use against
the Villains.
>> Yup.
>> And the cool thing was,
immediately, all five players
agreed.
When we do find it, we'll find
it as a tribe, and that is a
unified front.
And we're all in agreement on
that.
We're now fighting the good
fight as a team, and that's the
most positive thing to come from
today was realizing that we are
now a tribe of five that is very
ready to take on the Villains.
>> Are you with us?
>> Well, I'll admit, this
morning I woke up, I didn't
know where my head was at or
where I was going, or...
whatever, and now, I'm...
It's like the sun came out, and
I'm, like, "You know what?
It's pretty clear as day to me
now."
>> You know, I don't want to
swear on my family or anything.
I'm so... with me, you and
Coach.
That's who I want.
>> Hey, Coach, come here.
>> Sit down, Coach.
You know, man, I want to...
I don't how else to explain that
you can trust me.
You and Jerri I want to take to
the top three.
That's what I want.
That's what...
From the bottom of my heart,
that's what I want.
Parvati-- I don't think I can
beat her for the million.
I want to take you all to the
top three, man, and that's what
what I want.
>> Russell is empowered by this
game, because with all the
gullible people out here, he
thinks that he can outtalk
anybody.
So next thing I know, when I
come over there to join the
conversation-- after I'm
beckoned over, because I don't
want to seem paranoid and go
right up and listen in or say,
"What's going on?"-- Russell is
just sitting there just
spinning a pure line of gold,
and Jerri's just hook, line and
sinker.
>> I'm telling you that I've
made my decision, and I hope and
pray that you're going to be
there, 'cause you are the only
other person in this game that I
can literally look at in the
eyes, and say, "I trust you
100%."
And if it's just Russell and not
you, I'm not going to feel
comfortable, 'cause I've been
with you since day one.
>> Yeah, Jerri and I are
honor-bound to play this game
together, but if Jerri says,
"I'm in this wholeheartedly with
Russell," I really have no
choice.
So, it's just... It's just...
I don't know.
It's just, the waters are so
muddy right now...
and Jerri has muddied them.
>> Honestly, what Russell pulled
off last night at Tribal
Council-- it took huge balls.
I don't trust Rob.
We have a history, and we're
old school players, and all that
nonsense.
You know, I wanted to trust him
because of that, but I realize
Rob is not trustworthy.
He's not.
He proved it.
>> He proved it six years ago
when he was playing a different
game, and every time he said
he's going to vote for somebody
in this game so far, he's done
it, but I don't want to talk
about that first.
I'm kind of hurt, because you
sit there in front of Russell
and me and say, "Russell, I'm
in.
I just hope that Coach is, too,
but I'm in.
I hope he makes the same
decision."
You didn't talk to me about it.
You know, I mean, that...
I think that's what hurts.
You want to lump me and Russell
together in terms of trust.
That's crazy.
I mean, you just said right now
that, you know, basically, that
you trust he and I equal, and I
hope that that's not the case...
>> No, it's not.
>> ...because, you know that
you've had bad feelings about
Russell.
>> It's not the case.
I'll clear that up right now.
It's not the case, because...
You know, it's just not.
And, I mean, you and I are in a
really good position, and I'm...
It just...
You know what?
It just finally made sense to
me.
>> I just can't believe you just
threw all your eggs into
Russell's basket.
>> Well... I wouldn't say, all
my eggs.
So as much as I like Coach, that
guy is so naive.
Like, Russell is in this game to
play it, and he's in it to win
it.
And you know what?
So am I.
So as much as I like Coach, and
as much as I trust him, I mean,
I don't see someone who gets it,
like, in the grand scheme of
this game.
He's almost dead set against
manipulating anybody.
He wants to be the good guy to
everyone, and you can't.
You can't be the good guy to
everyone and win this game.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
>> Yes.
>> Let's do it!
>> PROBST: First things first.
I will take back the individual
immunity necklaces from last
time.
Thank you, Candice.
Thanks, Rob.
Individual immunity-- not today.
Tribal immunity is once again
back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, three
members of each tribe will race
relay-style up a platform and
across a net.
You'll then climb up a large
rope web to retrieve bags of
puzzle pieces.
Once you've collected all six
bags, the two remaining tribe
members must use those pieces
to solve a puzzle.
First tribe to get it right wins
immunity, guaranteed at least
one more day in this game.
Losers go to Tribal Council
where somebody will be voted
out.
Villains, you have three extra
members.
Cannot sit out the same people
in back-to-back challenges.
Who are the three you're gonna
sit out?
>> Myself, Danielle and Russell.
>> PROBST: Jerri, Danielle and
Russell sitting out.
Take a spot on the bench.
We'll get started.
Running for the Heroes, we have
Rupert, Colby and Candice.
On the puzzle, J.T. and Amanda.
Running for the Villains--
Parvati, Courtney, Coach.
On the puzzle-- Boston Rob and
Sandra.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Rupert!
>> PROBST: Rupert on the busted
toe.
Parvati dives head first.
>> That's it, Parvati.
>> PROBST: Rupert takes a
tumble.
Got to get up that rope web.
Get down with a bag.
Parvati has hers.
Rupert has his!
>> Hold on...
>> Come on, Rupert!
>> Come on, Parvati.
(Russell grunts)
>> PROBST: Rupert falling down
again.
Got to be hard to run on that
toe.
>> Courtney!
>> Let's go, Courtney! Let's go!
>> PROBST: Go, Courtney, go!
Go, Candice!
>> Go, Courtney!
(Courtney gasps)
>> PROBST: Courtney goes down.
Candice goes down.
>> Go, Courtney!
>> PROBST: Like running on a
trampoline.
>> Come on, Candice!
>> PROBST: Courtney and Candice.
Courtney has the second bag for
the Villains.
She drops and pops.
>> Go ahead, Courtney!
>> Go, Courtney!
>> PROBST: Candice lost some
time for the Heroes.
Go, Coach!
>> Here you go, Coach!
Come on, boy!
>> PROBST: Go, Colby.
Colby tried to take the side,
thinking that will help, but it
doesn't.
Coach is down with the third
bag for the Villains.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Colby has the third
bag for the Heroes.
>> Come on, Colby!
>> Come on!
(shouting)
>> PROBST: Parvati back out on
the course for her second bag.
>> Go!
>> Go, Parvati!
>> PROBST: Rupert back out on
the course for his second bag.
>> You got it, Parvati!
(overlapping shouting)
>> PROBST: Parvati has to go
high now, way high.
She has it, it drops... on her
booty and pops right up.
Rupert has the fourth bag for
the Heroes.
(overlapping shouting)
>> PROBST: Go, Courtney.
>> Courtney! Courtney!
>> PROBST: Go, Candice.
Courtney, once again, falls.
>> Come on, Courtney!
You got it!
>> PROBST: Candice running it.
She's learned from her first
time.
Candice just made up a lot of
time for the Heroes.
>> It's all you!
>> Grab it!
>> PROBST: Candice has her bag.
>> Go, Courtney!
>> PROBST: Courtney's
struggling.
>> It's all right! It's okay!
>> Jump, Courtney!
>> PROBST: Courtney does not
want to jump.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Fall flat!
Candice back with her second
bag.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Colby heading out for
that last bag for the Heroes.
>> Come on, Colby.
>> PROBST: Courtney lost a ton
of time for the Villains.
>> Come on.
>> PROBST: Go, Coach.
>> Get it, Colby!
>> Come on, Colby!
>> PROBST: Colby has the sixth
bag for the Heroes.
He drops and pops right up.
>> You got it!
Go, Coach!
>> PROST: Once he touches that
mat, start working on the
puzzle.
>> Go, Coach!
>> PROBST: Coach has the sixth
bag for the Villains.
Faster you get back, the more
time you have to work on that
puzzle.
>> Lot of time.
>> PROBST: Start working on the
puzzle.
>> It's a puzzle, you guys.
We got it.
>> PROBST: J.T. and Amanda
working together for the Heroes.
Sandra and Boston Rob working
together for the Villains.
It's no secret, Rob very good
at puzzles.
Heroes have had their hands full
going up against the Villains
when it involved a puzzle.
Big immunity on the line.
Heroes lose, they will be down
to four tribe members left in
this game.
A lot of pieces to this puzzle.
Patience will pay off.
J.T. and Amanda starting to
piece it together.
Heroes getting closer.
>> Come on, guys.
>> PROBST: Rob and Sandra
falling behind.
>> Let's go, guys. Let's go.
>> Don't panic.
Relax, relax.
>> PROBST: J.T. and Amanda doing
a great job on this puzzle,
expanding the lead.
Rob and Sandra switching sides,
trying to mix it up a little.
Will it help?
Heroes only a few pieces away.
Rob and Sandra struggling,
scrambling.
It's not going to matter.
>> Nice square.
>> PROBST: Four pieces left for
the Heroes.
Three pieces.
Two.
One.
(cheering)
Heroes win immunity!
>> Yes!
Yes! Yes!
>> Good job, guys.
>> We did it! We did it!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Heroes,
congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you, Jeff!
>> PROBST: No Tribal Council
tonight.
>> Yes! Thank you.
>> PROBST: Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Nice work.
Villains, Tribal Council
tonight.
One of the eight of you going
home.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
See you at Tribal.
>> I thought Courtney was
lagging.
Poor girl, you know, she was,
like, almost broken in half out
there.
We need to get rid of Courtney
tonight.
She's the weak link.
>> We just got back from our
immunity challenge, and got our
butts kicked.
Rob-- he got his butt kicked
today.
Sandra wasn't doing anything on
the puzzle.
Courtney looked like she was
about to break in half out
there.
It was one of the most pitiful
performances I have ever seen.
Yeah, right now, the Heroes are
starting to win.
Uh, we have to do something.
>> What do you think?
>> I think we need to weed off
the weak.
>> Who do you suggest?
>> One of these.
>> One of who?
>> Right here.
What do you want me to say?
>> I don't know.
>> You want me to be, you
know...?
>> That's not a way to gather
friends, I don't think.
>> Well, you know.
>> (laughing): How do you two
feel about that?
>> I don't like it.
>> Oh, no, I think...
I think he's right.
>> What kind of logic is that,
Russell?
That's a new one.
>> No hard feelings for nobody.
It's really just a game for me.
I don't put my...
>> I don't think I ever quite
heard that...
Sit with someone and tell
someone that, I want to vote you
or you off.
I never heard that approach
before.
>> You never?
>> No.
>> You'd be amazed how good that
approach works sometimes.
>> That's a new one.
>> Well, if Rob's gonna vote for
one of us, he's obviously not
going to say it in front of us,
and we're not gonna vote for
ourselves.
>> Oh, I'm not gonna vote for
one of you.
>> All Rob wants is to keep his
alliance strong, which I
understand, 'cause he knows,
once Courtney leaves, he's at my
mercy.
I'm after him.
He's after me.
May the best man win.
Whoever's better in the game--
that's which one is going to be
here longer, and it's going to
be me, and he sees it coming.
>> Tough one.
What's the plan?
>> We've got two decisions.
Blindside Parvati, or get rid
of Courtney and regroup the
alliance.
'Cause that was pathetic today,
dude, and I...
Dude, in Courtney, man, I don't
know what you see, man.
She is the w...
We have to dance around every
challenge because of Courtney.
And Sandra.
>> She's loyal.
I mean, that's something that
you value, right?
It's something I value, too.
You really think Parvati's more
of a threat than Russell at this
point?
I'll make a strong case for
Russell because I think he's
dangerous, Coach.
And from day one, I haven't
trusted him, and I don't...
I still don't.
Not that I trust Parvati,
either.
But, I mean, how does Jerri
feel?
>> I haven't talked to her.
I talked to you first 'cause
you're my right-hand man.
I mean, dude, I'm telling you
right now, as sure as anything,
I want to be standing there with
you on the last day.
>> We will be. We will be.
>> All right.
>> You have my word.
I'm voting for Russell.
I have yours?
>> Yup.
>> Okay.
>> Let's get that little bastard
out of here.
>> That's it. That's it.
You know, one way to make
somebody do what you want them
to do is to find what they hold
dear.
With Coach, it's his reputation
for being loyal.
And put that on the line.
You're saying that you're
giving your word, and that
you're the most loyal?
You better do what you say you
do, or let it be known that
you're a liar.
>> All right, well, Courtney
tonight, and then it will be
Sandra.
Get rid of them two snakes right
off the bat.
>> Where's Parvati?
>> She's back at camp, I think.
>> I know, man. You know what?
He's been trying to get rid of
you since day one, and that
takes a pretty big man to not
make the target.
>> Right. I mean, I'm trying to
keep the team strong.
He's constantly trying to get
rid of me.
>> Constantly.
>> We got to... We got...
I tell you, mean, we got...
>> I want to so bad.
>> I know you do.
>> You're a big man for not,
though.
I got to give it to you.
>> I know. We could do it now.
>> Let's think about this.
>> That's just disgusting, man.
>> Let's think about this a
while.
Me and Coach-- we can beat any
two guys they pair up.
I don't care. In anything.
>> Wow.
>> We can all do that, man.
We can...
>> Right, now, but I just...
I feel like the right thing to
do is Courtney.
It's going to make our tribe
stronger.
I feel like the right thing to
do is Courtney.
>> What do you think, Jerri?
>> I mean, what's the positive
of keeping Rob in, besides
keeping the tribe strong?
He's a mover and a shaker.
>> I say we can.
>> I mean, he can't be trusted.
>> And you agree with it, and
she agrees with it.
Parvati would.
That's four votes, Coach.
>> Come on, man.
>> I'm ready to get rid of that
fool.
>> I know. Let's not do it.
I don't feel right about it.
>> Why?
>> Yeah. Why?
>> It's the perfect time before
the merge.
>> Dude, I don't feel right
about it.
>> Dude, I feel the merge is
coming.
>> Rob is, like, the biggest
threat right now.
>> If you give me your word,
I'll believe you.
>> I'm with you guys 100%.
I came here to win this game.
Not at all costs.
I don't want Boston Rob to go
home.
That's what you can see on my
face right now.
I don't want him going home.
He doesn't deserve to go home.
He deserves to be here and play
this game.
I can't go back on my word.
I mean, I just gave those guys
my word because Russell crammed
it down our throats, and Jerri's
being gullible, and just saying,
okay, whatever.
And then I'm sitting there like
a fish out of water.
What am I going to do?
So now, if I go against them,
then, you know, I broke my word.
I want to be true to Boston Rob.
(sighs)
>> This game is such a trip.
>> They're coming after me.
>> You think so?
>> They want me out?
>> I don't know. I'm asking you.
>> Oh, I don't know.
>> No?
It's hard.
Don't sweat it, Jerri, you know?
It's a hard decision.
You got to do what's best for
you.
>> It's giving me a headache,
man.
>> Do what you think is best
for you.
I don't even see it as that much
of a choice.
Like, you know what to do.
(Jerri laughs)
You do, but you're...
I am at your mercy.
I don't have a leg to stand on.
>> I mean, you know, I would
love to just go, "Hey, Rob, you
know, I trust you 100%," but...
>> But you shouldn't?
>> I can't.
>> But you can trust me in this
situation, because you can
always trust somebody when they
have... when their backs are
against the wall.
Because I don't really have any
other choice.
You're smart, Jerri.
You figure it out.
(Jerri laughs)
You know what to do.
(sighs)
>> I feel like I've aged, like,
five years in one day.
I mean, Rob literally told me...
He said, "Look, Jerri, you know,
just do whatever you got to do
to get yourself as far in the
game as you can, and if it's at
my expense, I... I understand.
It's a game."
>> You know that it's not the
right time to get rid of Boston
Rob, right?
'Cause if that happens, you
know, like, challenge-wise, I'm
not for that at all.
At all.
>> I'm not a good villain.
(Jerri laughs)
>> Not a good what?
>> I'm not a good villain.
I'm just not.
>> PROBST: For the first 15 days
of this game, you guys were
dominating, but then, the Heroes
have stumbled onto this magic
number of five and have
destroyed you guys.
So, Sandra, how is tonight's
vote different?
Before, you guys thought you had
no competition out there.
>> Um, I think we're all over
the board.
It's going to be all kinds of
names and numbers out there
today.
I don't know what to tell you,
Jeff.
>> PROBST: Coach, if Sandra's
right, is that indicative of a
tribe in trouble?
>> I think that at the dawn of
every morning, hope springs
eternal.
I personally saw, with the
absence of Tyson, not only a
great competitor, but also
somebody that kind of bridged
the gap.
>> PROBST: Where's the gap?
>> I mean, you've got, um, you
know, Sandra and Courtney.
They're tight with Boston Rob.
And then you've got Danielle,
Russell and Parvati.
And that's another group.
And then you've got Jerri and I
have been the floaters.
So, as you can see, it's just
like everybody is going in
different directions.
And Tyson was the guy, in my
opinion, that bridged that gap.
>> Well, see, I don't agree with
that at all.
>> I disagree with that
completely.
>> I think by getting rid of
him, it solidified a stronger
group of people.
>> PROBST: But Danielle, you and
Russell disagreeing with what
Coach says confirms what Coach
says.
>> People can have different
opinions, even if they're on
the same tribe.
>> PROBST: Rob, you had one of
the craziest Tribal Councils
last time that I've ever seen--
20 seasons.
This is not a tribe that's
working together.
>> It's not a tribe that's
And I agree with Coach.
I think losing Tyson was a big
mistake, and it hurt us
tremendously.
>> But I could have blindsided
anybody that night.
My alliance, Parvati, was about
to go home.
So I made the best move I
thought that was possible.
And it was my decision.
>> And a lot of people are mad
about it, and a lot of people
haven't gotten over it, and it
shows in challenges.
>> I personally don't think that
that's true.
I think that a lot of us are
giving 100%, but everybody is
so damn paranoid about
alliances, and it's going to
continue to be like that.
>> It's catastrophic, because
some people are thinking in
terms of keeping their alliance
strong, instead of keeping the
team strong.
>> Well, you know what?
He put my name down.
He didn't know I was going to
blindside Tyson.
That's keeping the team strong?
>> I think it is keeping the
team strong.
>> I'm going to use Rob's quote.
"If you ain't with me, you're
against me."
>> That's right, and you are
against me.
It's clear.
And, I mean, there's been no
secret about that, Russell.
What I'm saying, my idea of
trust and loyalty is different
from Russell's.
>> Loyalty?
I put my butt on the line for
my...
>> I saw what you did.
>> ...for my people.
>> I was willing to go home.
If that ain't loyal, I don't
know what is.
I don't think you have the guts
to do what I did last Tribal.
>> Okay, you're entitled to your
opinion.
>> If you're gunning for me,
you're not going to get what you
want, not with me.
You're going to have to go.
>> PROBST: Coach, where's your
level of trust with these guys?
>> I mean, I see two soldiers on
opposite ends of the spectrum.
You hear the fight in both of
them.
You hear the independence in
both of them.
So, I know that the lines have
been drawn in the sand today,
but I'm begging you guys to
reconsider and keep this tribe
strong.
I mean, we can still win every
single challenge, but not if our
best competitors are going to be
at war with each other.
>> But at some point, you pick
someone to trust, and you go
with that, and that's all there
is to do, and I did that.
And I think tonight's vote is
going to be to bring this tribe
closer together.
>> PROBST: Jerri, literally,
you're sitting in the middle of
this group, and your name has
not come up at all.
>> I've been confronted, one by
one by, by everybody in this
tribe, and both sides have some
positives and some negatives,
and I've tried to weigh both.
So I'm forced to make a
decision, and I'm hoping that
it's the right one, and I don't
know for sure if it is,
sometimes, but I have decided
that I have to believe it is.
>> PROBST: Well, there's no
doubt that tonight's Tribal
Council is going to mark a
turning point for this tribe.
Let's get to it.
Danielle, you're up.
>> It's game over.
It's either you or me.
>> I'm making a choice tonight
in hopes that this will be right
for me in the end.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Rob.
Russell.
Rob.
Two votes-- Rob, one vote--
Russell.
We're tied.
Two votes-- Rob, two votes--
Russell.
Rob.
That's three votes Rob.
Tied again.
Three votes-- Rob, three votes--
Russell.
Courtney.
That's three votes-- Rob, three
votes-- Russell, one vote--
Courtney.
One vote left.
Eighth person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs. Villains--
Rob.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> PROBST: Rob, the tribe has
spoken.
Well, that is without question,
the biggest move this tribe has
made in the game thus far.
Good news is, not going to take
long at all to find out if
voting out Rob brings this tribe
back together or destroys it.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor-- the competition gets
dirty, but the real battle is at
the Villain's camp, where every
alliance crumbles.
>> Coach is a pathological liar.
>> Russell is a bully.
>> Every single person on this
team is an idiot.
>> I can't stand Jerri, I hate
Coach, I hate Danielle, I hate
Russell even more.
Why are you blaming me and
Courtney?
>> No.
>> Pray for the merge.
>> I mean, I saw it coming
tonight.
It's tough.
These guys-- they knew what they
were doing.
You know, I wish Coach would
have kept his word.
I pretty much knew that he was
going to do what he thought was
in his best interest.
I did as much as I could for my
tribe to put them on my
shoulders and carry them as long
as I could, but at the end of
the day, this is what I get in
thanks.