>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
Although there were only five
Heroes left, they appeared to be
a tight-knit group.
>> Best team on Survivor
right here.
>> PROBST: But their unity was
only an illusion because when
J.T. found a hidden immunity
idol, Amanda and Candice decided
he wasn't as trustworthy as
they thought.
>> J.T.'s the slimiest
guy out here.
>> PROBST: The Heroes had also
convinced themselves that the
Villains tribe was completely
controlled by women.
>> Sure looks like they got
a woman's alliance.
>> PROBST: But there was no
women's alliance.
>> The Hero tribe thinks this is
an all-girl alliance.
They think I'm on the outside,
when I'm the leader.
>> PROBST: In fact, two of the
women, Sandra and Courtney, were
in the greatest danger.
>> We're the ones on the outs.
>> PROBST: When the Villains
lost their fourth challenge
in a row...
Heroes win immunity!
(Heroes cheer)
...Courtney was the next to go.
But Sandra made a brilliant move
to save her friend.
She convinced Russell that Coach
had turned on him.
>> Russell's so stupid.
He ate that crap up.
>> PROBST: Her plan worked.
Courtney was spared,
and Coach was voted out...
Coach, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving Jerri without
her closest ally.
11 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
We went to Tribal Council and
we went ahead and voted out
Coach because I told Russell
that Coach was going to vote
for him.
And that's why Coach is probably
now out there looking into the
sky wondering where everything
went wrong.
>> I didn't see that coming
at all.
I had no idea that Coach was
gonna go tonight.
Not a clue.
I'm not next, am I?
>> No way, no way, no way.
>> Oh, God.
>> You have my word.
I will not write your name down,
I promise you that.
Obviously, it was last-minute,
and I didn't want to tell you
'cause I didn't want to freak
you out.
>> Okay.
>> Don't worry.
>> Yeah... I don't want to be
next.
>> You're not going to.
(Jerri laughs)
>> Coach was my one and only
serious alliance.
I mean, he's the only person
out here I trusted, so I'm still
going to stick true to the
alliance that I created with
Russell, Parvati and Danielle,
but at this point, that's all I
got.
>> So, what happened?
>> You didn't know it was going
to happen?
>> I had a strong feeling that I
wasn't going to write his name
down.
Coach betrayed me by telling
Sandra that he was trying to
blindside me tonight.
>> I just wanted to make sure
that I wasn't next...
>> No, I... I promise you, you
ain't next.
>> Okay.
>> You see, we got five girls
on my tribe now.
I feel great about it, because
I trust three of them.
But I don't trust Sandra and
Courtney, so they'll be the next
to go.
I promise you that.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Treemail!
>> Yeah.
>> Treemail. Treemail.
>> Oh, what is this?
>> "Your next reward challenge
requires endurance and a
threshold for pain.
You would have seen this
challenge in Survivor:
Tocantins.
Each survivor will position
themselves between two narrow
walls, their feet perched on a
small foothold."
>> Hmm.
>> "This time, you will each be
paired against a member of the
other tribe.
Below you must rank your five
competitors from strongest to
weakest.
This will determine who you
match up against-- the person
with the same ranking from the
other tribe."
>> Coach screamed at the end of
his, and was, like... (yelling)
(laughter)
>> He did.
>> Jumped off, you guys.
>> Strongest. I'm obviously the
strongest, but I'm the heaviest,
too.
>> I think maybe all the girls
should play.
>> Yeah.
>> We have little feet.
We're lighter.
>> So do I.
>> I think we have an upper
hand against them, five women.
>> So do I.
>> Me and Danielle both won
our endurance challenge.
>> They're going to put all the
guys at the top, 'cause it says,
put your strongest to your
weakest, and, you know, they're
guys with big egos.
>> I'll be able to do great at
this.
>> You think you're going to do
the best?
>> Yeah.
>> The bigger you are, the
harder it is.
>> If you guys want to put me
weakest, that's fine.
>> No, no, no.
>> I'll tell you the weakest if
you're too proud to take it,
though.
(Rupert laughs)
>> I think I'm the strongest of
all 11 of us still left out
here, but if they want to rank
me as the weakest, I'll let
them.
>> Last time, the bigger people
went out first.
>> Right.
>> I mean, small girls with
small feet are really what can
do really well at it.
>> I would love to see all five
of us still up there, and three
of them just drop out.
(Rupert laughs)
Just to make a... make a
statement.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Heroes getting your first look
at the new Villain tribe.
>> PROBST: Coach voted out at
the last Tribal Council, and
Coach became the first member of
our jury.
Rupert, what's the reaction to
seeing it's Coach that is now
gone from the game?
>> Phew!
Cannot believe Coach is gone,
you know.
But that women's alliance looks
very strong.
It's kind of obvious.
>> PROBST: J.T., obvious to you
guys it's a woman's alliance?
>> I would have bet my life
Russell or Coach-- one was going
to be gone.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's reward
challenge?
(all voicing assent)
For today's challenge, you will
use your arms to brace yourself
between two walls while your
bare feet are perched on very
narrow footholds.
Every ten minutes, you will move
to an even smaller foothold.
Once you reach the third and
final foothold, you will stay
there for as long as you can.
Each person will be matched up
against someone from the
opposite tribe.
All you have to do to score a
point-- outlast your opponent.
First tribe to score three
points wins reward.
>> PROBST: Want to know what
your playing for?
(all voicing assent)
Well, it's clear you all like to
live adventurously, so let me
tell you what is at stake.
The winning tribe will receive
a feast from Outback Steakhouse.
>> ALL: Oh!
>> Bloomin' onion, baby!
>> PROBST: Steak, shrimp on the
barbie...
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: ...loaded baked
potato with all the fixings.
So much food from Outback
Steakhouse, you will not be able
to eat it all.
(Rupert laughs)
This morning in your treemail,
you were asked to rank your
tribe to determine our matchups,
and in doing so, Villains, you
decided who you were sitting
out.
Russell sitting out this
challenge.
Take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, take your
positions, and we'll get
started.
Some interesting match-ups.
Danielle and Candice.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Courtney taking on
Amanda.
Parvati taking on J.T., who won
this in the Tocantins.
>> Hey, Colby.
>> Hi, Jerri.
>> PROBST: A rematch-- Jerri
Manthey, Colby Donaldson-- going
all the way back to season two.
And another rematch-- Sandra and
Rupert going back to the Pearl
Islands, our seventh season.
>> Love you.
>> PROBST: Go ahead and head on
up.
First round is ten minutes.
You can't use your back, your
butt, your hips, your shoulders.
Forearms are totally fine.
If you want to lean your head
against it, if that helps,
that's okay.
Everybody's looking good right
now.
(Jerri exhales loudly)
This challenge is officially on.
Both ranked your tribe,
theoretically, from strongest to
weakest, but judging from the
fact that J.T. is in the middle,
I'm guessing there was some
strategy about who the other
tribe was going to put up, and
that affected the positions you
chose.
Since you're resting comfortably
early on in this challenge, we
have a little bit of a
celebration to note.
Today marks the one hundredth
day that Amanda has played
Survivor.
First person to get to 100 days.
>> Yay!
>> You go, girl.
>> PROBST: Okay, it is time to
move down to the next smaller
foothold.
Five, four...
three, two, one.
Everybody looks good.
All you have to do is outlast
your opponent, and you score a
point.
First to three wins the Outback
Steakhouse reward.
>> I love Outback Steakhouse.
Before my husband left to
Afghanistan, that whole week,
twice we went there.
>> PROBST: Really?
>> That's his spot.
>> PROBST: So if you win, not
only are you going to get a full
belly, you got some emotional
attachment there.
>> The fact that J.T. thinks
this is an all-girl alliance
gives me a perfect opportunity,
once we merge, to make him think
I'm flipping.
I done planted that little
Russell seed in their mind, and
it's taken root, and they
believe it.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to move down to the third and
final foothold.
If you fall off during this
time, you are out of the
challenge.
We could lose somebody right
here.
>> This peg is little.
>> PROBST: Three, two, one.
Everybody's in position.
This is where you're going to
stay for the rest of the
challenge.
Your feet are now perched on a
foothold that is about a
quarter-inch wide.
Now, it's going to get a little
tougher.
It'll start to hurt a little
bit.
Everybody's got to dig deep.
(Colby panting)
Colby readjusting, trying to
find a sweet spot, somewhere
that doesn't hurt.
Once it starts to hurt, it's
tough to get rid of the pain.
Colby drops out.
Jerri scores the first point for
the Villains.
Jerri can step down.
>> Hells yeah.
>> PROBST: Don't lose your
concentration.
>> Come on, girls.
>> PROBST: Jerri scores for the
Villains.
Villains now have one point.
You only need three.
Parvati readjusting now.
(exhales)
Rupert fighting through the
pain.
Rupert with a broken toe.
Trying to hold on.
>> Hang on Sandra.
You popped out some babies; this
ain't nothing.
>> Two of them-- didn't even get
a aspirin.
(laughs)
Two natural births.
>> Yeah, you got it.
>> Be strong, Rupe.
>> PROBST: Beads of sweat
pouring off of Rupert's face.
>> You got it, Rupe.
You got it, buddy.
Get in the zone.
>> PROBST: Rupert slobbering
now, he's struggling so hard.
Rupert is out of the challenge.
Sandra can step down.
>> One more minute.
>> PROBST: Villains now have two
points.
(laughs)
>> Sorry, guys.
>> PROBST: The Villains need
just one more point.
If J.T., Amanda or Candice fall
out of this challenge before
their opponent, it's over for
the Heroes.
Parvati readjusting again,
trying to find some way to ease
the pain.
Amanda struggling a bit.
>> Courtney, yep.
She's shaking, Courtney, she's
shaking.
>> PROBST: It could come down to
this: Courtney versus Amanda.
They played this game together
in China.
>> Courtney, hold on, Courtney.
>> PROBST: Amanda needs to dig
deep right now.
Amanda drops out.
Villains win reward!
(excited shouting)
>> Oh, my God, oh, my God!
Are you crying?
(laughs)
Nice work.
>> PROBST: Heroes, after four
straight wins, got nothing for
you.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
>> Bye, guys.
(laughs)
>> Wah-mbulance.
>> PROBST: All right, Villains,
congratulations.
Grab your stuff, head out and
enjoy it.
>> Thank you.
(ice rattling)
>> Cheers.
>> To winning.
>> Yay!
>> Cheers, Villains.
>> Cheers.
>> Oh, my God, that's so good.
>> Villains forever.
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> This is delicious.
(sucking air through straw)
>> You're ready for another one,
Sandra.
>> Sandra, is that their cue?
>> You were drinking it?
Sandra put one down.
>> Come here, homie.
Give me that, homie.
>> Yeah!
>> My husband is a soldier in
the army, and I kind of felt bad
I was without my husband because
I'm sure he wishes he was at
Outback Steakhouse, too, because
we just love Outback.
We always go to Outback, but,
you know, he's got to do his job
and I got to do what I have to
do out here on Survivor.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Thank you, Lord, for this
meal.
>> Thank you so much, Lord.
>> Thank you.
>> Wow.
>> Yay.
>> I've been wanting a salad for
ages.
>> Oh, my God, I'm using a
napkin.
(overlapping chatter)
So after the drinks, we go and
our table is set and, you know,
everyone is just diving into
their salads, and I picked up
the napkin and, like, flicked it
open, and this little, tiny
rolled up clue was inside my
napkin, and I was like, "Oh, my
gosh, I hope no one saw that."
I, like, stuffed it in my
underwear as fast as I could.
>> Oh, my stomach just said
thank you.
>> Wow.
>> This is so good.
You know, I knew it was a clue
to a hidden immunity idol.
I was like, "Oh, my gosh, I am
crazy lucky because I sat in the
corner next to Danielle and I'm
super lucky that it was in my
napkin."
>> If and when the merge
happens, all those guys over
there think that it's a girl
alliance.
It's just so funny that they
assume that.
>> Rupert, too, all the time,
he's like, "That all-female
alliance looks really strong."
>> He's like, "It's pretty
obvious.
It's so obvious.
I'd stake me pirate life on it."
>> Arr!
(laughter)
>> Perfect.
All the Heroes see is an all-
women's alliance.
First of all, there's no all-
girl alliance, and second of
all, Russell's running the show.
They have no idea what's going
on over here, and it's awesome.
(laughs)
>> Mmm.
>> There you go.
Look at that.
Thank you.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
Anything you wanted, the Outback
way.
>> Wow.
>> More shrimp and salad.
>> We're happy now.
>> I'm gonna eat enough food for
everybody.
>> This is good.
>> It's really good.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Mmm.
>> The best steak and potatoes
I've ever had in my whole life.
>> I'm definitely finishing it.
>> Yeah.
Guys, I'm full already.
>> You're full?
>> I'm full.
>> Oh, no.
>> I have to pee, though.
I'm gonna get out.
Pardon moi.
Danielle.
My napkin.
>> How did nobody else see you
get that?
>> I don't know, I just, like,
found it in my napkin and it
fell into my lap and I just
shoved it in my underwear.
>> Oh, my God.
>> "Another immunity idol is
hidden at your camp.
You want it in your possession,
but it does you no good if you
don't know when to use it."
I shared the clue with Danielle
just so Danielle knows, like,
I'm on her side.
I want Danielle to feel tighter
with me than she does with
anyone else.
>> You don't have a pocket or
anything?
>> No, but I can put it in my
boobs.
>> It was kind of a part of my
plan to make Danielle feel
really connected to me, so that
at the end of the game, she
feels more loyal to me so that
she'll protect me over Russell.
>> All right, perfect.
>> All right, potty break.
>> I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
>> We'll fill Russell in on a
need-to-know basis, and right
now Russell doesn't need to
know, so he's not going to know.
>> You know what?
I don't give a damn about steak.
I've eaten at least a thousand
steaks in my time.
(chuckles)
So I'm not gonna worry about a
damn steak when we got a game to
play, you know?
To hear that there were steaks
up for grabs was tough because,
you know, I live off steaks.
I raise cattle.
I cut my own steaks up, you
know.
We eat black angus beef right
off the farm.
But we didn't come out here to
win steaks.
We came out here to win the big
prize.
If we win this next immunity
challenge...
I got a plan.
>> Uh-oh, J.T.'s got a plan.
>> Let's hear it.
>> The next immunity challenge
guarantees us the finals.
>> Let's hear the plan.
>> But we're relying on the
merge.
I bet my life in this game on it
that we're going to merge.
Russell knows he's going next.
So, granted I get a chance to
talk to Russell at the next
immunity challenge and we win, I
give him the hidden immunity
idol, he votes out Parvati...
bam, done.
>> How are you gonna give it to
him, though?
>> Hand it to him.
>> Wrapped up with a sheet of
paper with instructions on what
to do with it.
Parvati's gone.
>> Then pick the girls off.
>> Pick 'em off like sitting
ducks, then vote Russell's ass
out sixth.
>> I think it's really crazy to
give Russell the idol.
You don't know what's going on
over there.
He could be in with the girls
for all we know.
Like, we don't know.
What do you think about this
idea?
I mean, it could give us the
numbers and it gets the idol
away from him.
He just gives it up.
>> "Cross over the bridge to the
dancing trees."
Dancing trees?
>> Let's go look and see if any
look like they're dancing.
Danielle and I woke up this
morning and we're like quiet
little mice running around
because there's an immunity
idol hidden at our camp and we
didn't want Russell to see us.
>> Dancing... tree.
>> It's those right there, right
there.
You think?
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
>> They look like they're
dancing.
All right, so I guess look right
here.
>> Yeah.
It could be behind this.
It could be over here, too.
>> (laughing): Oh, my God.
>> What?
>> Oh, my God, we just found
that in, like, four seconds.
Here, hold this so I can cover
it up.
>> Nice.
>> We found the idol.
I am the happiest girl in the
world that I found that idol
because it gives me control of
the game right now.
This is a big deal.
Oh, my God, I can't believe we
have that.
And I'm not going to tell
Russell about the idol right
now.
I want Russell to be out of the
loop for a little bit.
I don't see anything wrong with
making him wait.
I really don't.
It doesn't mean I don't trust
him.
It's just...
I kind of want to see him squirm
a little bit.
It's fun.
(both laugh)
It's not all Russell running the
show around here.
He is not the king of Survivor.
I'm the queen.
(laughs)
And usually the king does what
the queen says anyway, so I'm
cool.
>> You're writing your letter to
Russell, buddy?
>> Yep.
"Russell, this is a huge turning
point in this game.
This is not fake.
I wouldn't waste your time
or mine.
Just by competing against you
and the few handshakes we've
had, I feel like I can
trust you.
Play the idol tonight and
save yourself.
All the girls should be writing
your name down, so act like you
know you're going home.
I think you should write
Parvati's name down to send
her home.
We will most likely merge at
ten people, and then you will
be completely safe with us.
Our five plus you will remain
strong until the girls are
done with.
We can then work on getting
ourselves into the final three."
>> This is your chance to show
you're not a villain.
>> I'll put that at the end
right here.
>> Good.
Oh, my gosh.
>> It could work, y'all.
If that works, it would be
incredible.
I'm really nervous.
I mean, I'm always nervous, but
I'm really nervous today because
I'm going to try the big
plan today.
>> If it all works, it's a
great plan.
>> If we win, I'm going to try
to give Russell my hidden
immunity idol, based on me
guessing that he's on the outs,
which I really feel like he is.
All right, this is our chance.
That will give us the numbers
going into the merge.
So, it's all up to us.
We have to win.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Oh, yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Candice-- give it up.
(Jeff chuckles)
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, both
tribes will start on a platform
floating in the water.
On my go, one member at a time
must move a bag of puzzle pieces
along a rope and through a
series of obstacles to your
finish mat.
Once you have all five bags, you
will use those puzzle pieces to
build a totem pole.
The first tribe to assemble it
correctly wins immunity, and
everybody on that tribe is
guaranteed a one-in-ten shot at
winning a million bucks.
Losers go to Tribal Council
where somebody's shot at that
million will come to an end.
Villains, you have one extra
person.
You sat out Russell last time.
Who is going to sit out this
challenge?
>> PROBST: Sandra, take a spot
on the bench.
Everybody else, take your spots.
We'll get started.
Here we go, for immunity!
Survivors ready?
Go!
Jerri for the Villains, and
Rupert for the Heroes.
Little different from some of
the other challenges in that you
are not attached to the rope,
just a bag of puzzle pieces.
(indistinct shouting)
Jerri now with a bit of a lead
for the Villains.
Just barely.
>> Come on, Rupert!
>> PROBST: Those bags take on
some water, they get a little
heavier.
Rupert now in the lead for the
Heroes.
>> There you go!
(indistinct shouting)
>> Come on, Rupert!
(whooping)
>> PROBST: Rupert flying through
this course now.
Jerri slowing down.
>> That's okay, Jerri!
Keep going!
>> PROBST: You don't want to
lose your lead early.
(indistinct shouting)
You may never catch up.
>> Come on, Rupert!
>> PROBST: Rupert heading to the
finish with that first bag for
the Heroes.
>> Run, Rupert! Run!
>> Go, Rupe!
Go, Rupert!
>> PROBST: Go, Heroes!
J.T. in the water for the Heroes
with that second bag.
>> Go, Jerri!
>> PROBST: Jerri now heading to
the finish for the Villains with
their first bag.
Go, Villains!
Danielle in the water for the
Villains.
J.T. going to be hard to catch
right now.
Danielle doing a nice job for
the Villains.
She's definitely made up some of
the time that Jerri lost.
>> Come on, Danielle!
>> PROBST: J.T. on the home
stretch with that second bag for
the Heroes.
Go, Heroes!
Amanda now in the water for the
Heroes.
Danielle is throwing herself
through this course...
>> Come on, Danielle!
>> PROBST: ...trying to make up
some time.
Amanda now gaining on Danielle.
Danielle has the second bag
for the Villains.
>> You got it.
>> PROBST: Amanda has the third
bag for the Heroes.
Danielle now sprinting to the
end for the Villains with her
second bag.
Go, Villains!
Parvati in the water for the
Villains.
Amanda moving fairly quickly
through this last stage of the
challenge.
Now Amanda's heading back with
that third bag of puzzles pieces
for the Heroes.
Go, Heroes!
>> We got it, Parvati!
>> PROBST: Candice now on the
course with the fourth bag for
the Heroes.
Parvati's through the final
obstacle very quickly for the
Villains.
Go, Villains!
Courtney now in the water for
the Villains.
>> PROBST: Candice heading back
with that fourth bag for the
Heroes.
>> PROBST: Go, Colby!
Colby in the water for the
Heroes with that fifth and final
bag.
(thunder crackling)
Rain starting to come down now
in the middle of this challenge.
Colby launches himself over the
tall obstacle.
Courtney now heading back with
that fourth bag for the
Villains.
Go, Russell!
Russell in the water for the
Villains.
Colby with a huge lead for the
Heroes.
(indistinct shouting)
Russell is going to have to be
Superman out there.
(indistinct shouting)
Colby racing back with that
fifth and final bag for the
Heroes.
Start working on your puzzle.
Russell doing his best to make
up time for the Villains.
>> You got it, Russell!
>> I got the middle.
I got the middle.
Give him the middle.
>> Get it up, man.
>> PROBST: Heroes making quick
work of this puzzle.
>> Go, Russell!
>> PROBST: Heroes very close.
(thunder rumbling)
Heroes win immunity!
>> Yeah!
(whooping)
>> Good job, Russell.
>> Good job, guys.
>> Would you like your dinner?
>> Cocktails...
(overlapping chatter)
>> PROBST: Heroes,
congratulations once again.
>> Yeah, baby!
>> Yes!
>> Good job.
>> No problem.
>> PROBST: For the third
straight time, Heroes win
immunity.
No tribal Council.
Everybody's safe.
Villains, after 24 days, one of
you going home tonight.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who it's going to be.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
I will see you tonight at
Tribal.
>> Now, I don't even have to
find idols.
People are actually giving me
idols.
You don't hand the enemy the
idol, especially when his name
is Russell Hantz.
You don't do that.
That's a no-no.
(bird squawking)
>> Damn, we did it, and we got
the idol out to Russell, and we
know he's going to be on our
side.
(sighing)
Serves them damn Villains right.
We'll make Survivor history with
this one today, guys.
>> I think so.
>> Yeah.
(Rupert laughing)
>> With Russell getting that
hidden immunity idol, he's
probably beaming with
excitement.
Russell is probably having
trouble containing himself right
now.
(Parvati laughing)
>> "Russell, read in complete
privacy."
(Parvati laughing)
"This is a huge turning point in
this game.
This is not fake.
I wouldn't waste your time or
mine.
Hopefully, we are on the same
page.
Play the idol tonight."
>> For sure.
>> "To save yourself..."
>> Save myself?
>> Because clearly, you're on
the outside of an all-devouring
female alliance.
>> Right.
>> I put that part in myself.
"All the girls should be writing
your name down, so act like you
know you're going home."
I can't believe he's writing all
this, like...
>> He's telling me what to do.
He's-He's giving me pointers.
How do you give the idol king an
idol?
"Here, Mr. Russell.
Here's an idol.
This one's just for you."
Well, thank you.
You know what?
I think J.T. just handed me one
million dollars.
Hey, I guess he can afford it.
>> "I think you should write
Parvati's name down and send
her home."
(Parvati laughs)
Why is everyone throwing me
under the bus?
They don't even know what's
going on over here.
Okay.
"Our five plus you will remain
strong till the girls are done
with."
>> "We can..."
>> "We can then work on getting
ourselves in the final three."
>> Wow, wonder what that means.
>> Big promises, J.T.
>> Yeah.
>> "Hopefully, I can trust you,
and you're not truly a villain."
>> Yes, I am.
>> "Let's do this together.
See you soon."
B.F.F., forever.
(both giggling)
X.O.X.O.
>> Love you.
>> "J.T.
Destroy this right when you
finish reading."
(laughter)
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I can't believe he
wrote you a letter.
Why would you hand a villain
your heart?
J.T. gave Russell his heart
today, and Russell is just going
to stab it a million times, a
million times over, and hand it
to me, and I'm going to eat it.
(laughing)
What are we, in fifth grade?
He's passing notes?
>> Wrote me a letter.
>> What is wrong with him?
Like, I cannot believe that kid
won.
>> Whatever. Ignore them.
There's nothing we can do now.
Well, this sucks, Sandra.
I'm sorry.
They're all in control, and
we're now scrambling like
cockroaches.
>> Look, that's how I was in my
season.
I was al... We were always in
control of everything.
>> So was I on mine.
And you know what?
Tables turn.
>> This is what we get for being
bitches.
Me and Courtney-- you know,
our morale is really low 'cause
it's inevitable that me or
Courtney are going home, and I'm
really sad, because me without
Courtney-- that's like rice
without beans, you know?
So it's up to Danielle, Parvati
and Russell who they're going to
vote out.
>> Yeah, Courtney.
>> Simple?
>> Simple.
>> Parv?
>> Yeah?
>> Done deal.
Now that we lost the challenge
today, we can get rid of
Courtney.
I don't trust Courtney or
Sandra.
But I don't like Courtney,
'cause I think she'll flip.
>> So are they gonna vote for me
or Sandra?
>> I don't know.
I don't know what to do, because
I wanted to keep you forever.
You know?
>> I know.
I mean, the only thing I can say
to you is that if we have five,
and if I'm there, Amanda is more
likely to come with us.
>> Yeah.
>> Because she trusts me.
Do you know what I mean?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> That's my only perk.
'Cause I would stay with you.
Well, whatever.
That's my argument for me.
I'm not going to throw Sandra
under the bus.
I wouldn't vote for her, either.
So I'm just going to vote for
Jerri, I guess, and whatever
happens, happens.
>> Look, you would definitely
stay with me?
>> Yeah.
>> Things are going to go crazy
as soon as we merge, because
it's five-five.
As long as I know you'll stick
with me, then I'll do what I can
do to keep you.
>> I'm... I'm...
>> But you have to be with me.
(laughter)
Courtney and I have become
really close, and, uh, I don't
know.
I want to keep Courtney here,
because I feel like, once
there's a merge, she would stay
more loyal to me than to
Russell.
I want to keep myself kind of
lower key on this one, because
if I try to save her too much,
people are going to think, "Oh,
she has something on the side
with Courtney."
(Parvati laughs)
>> They gave him their idol.
>> J.T. gave me their idol to
save me tonight.
>> Shut up!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Are you dying?
Are you dying?
>> Shut up.
>> Save yourself.
>> He did not do that.
>> They just think this girl
thing is way too strong.
>> They are so set on the girl
thing, which is why I want to
talk to you about Courtney,
because I think we need to keep
Courtney tonight.
>> Yeah.
>> I just think, Courtney would
be more likely to stick with us
than Sandra.
Do you trust that you have
Sandra's loyalty?
>> I don't trust Courtney at
all.
I-I think she'll flip, and then
all of a sudden...
>> I-I think Sandra will flip
way before Courtney.
>> All of a sudden, they have,
uh...
>> And she's more strategic.
>> I think they'll both flip, so
it just comes down to who's more
threatening...
>> All of a sudden, you got
Amanda talking to you.
>> ...as far as who can talk
better-- Sandra or Courtney?
>> Sandra, and who makes up lies
for no reason?
>> I just think Courtney is
way more likely to go flip-flop.
>> But then you have to look at,
like, if she gets to the end,
Sandra would be harder to beat
than Courtney.
>> Courtney would be easier
to stick to...
>> To keep track of.
>> For me.
>> I mean, it really doesn't
matter one way or the other with
me.
>> I feel like I can keep
Courtney in check more than I
can keep Sandra.
>> PROBST: We'll now bring in
the first member of our jury...
Coach, voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
Sandra, at the last Tribal
Council, trust was once again
the big theme.
Is that going to be the case
again tonight?
>> To me, it's like when I'm
sitting in the living room in
my house, whoever Jeff asks the
trust question to-- that's the
last person that should be
answering that question.
I'm in trouble.
I know I am, because Tyson was
in my alliance.
He's gone.
Boston Rob was in my alliance.
And today, it's between me and
Courtney.
One of us two is going.
>> PROBST: Is that right,
Courtney?
Is that what you think, as well?
It's you or Sandra?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Russell, is there any
correlation to the fact that
Sandra and Courtney are also the
people who sit out, by far, the
most often in challenges?
>> No, not to me.
It's always that same question--
who can I trust the most?
>> PROBST: Danielle, what is it
about Sandra and her
trustworthiness or lack thereof
that has her name coming up
tonight?
>> That she's not in my
alliance, and I've seen how
she's playing the game, and
she's able to manipulate people.
>> PROBST: Give me an example.
>> Yeah, me, too.
Give me an example.
>> Okay, um, I've seen you put
into people's minds different
things that maybe weren't true
just to stir the pot up.
>> PROBST: But Danielle, the
question was trustworthiness,
not big mouth.
>> Well, that's kind of...
She's just not been on my side.
>> PROBST: That's just not doing
what you want her to do.
>> Me and Boston Rob were
together from the beginning,
but then it comes down to me,
because now I'm the one left.
>> No, no, no.
Rob and you decided to not talk
to me and pull in Courtney and
Tyson, and I had nowhere to go.
So, what was I supposed to do?
>> That didn't have nothing to
do with Sandra.
>> Yeah, but you were a part of
it, and you didn't make me
feel like...
>> Make you feel how, if you're
running off with Parvati and
Russell?
Make you feel how?
>> Well, you were running off...
>> Why should I come to you and
say hello when you don't come
and say hello to me?
>> You were Rob's, like,
sidekick.
Whatever Rob said to do, you
went and did, and he said to
watch...
>> And that's exactly what you
do with Parvati.
She's the boss, and you do
whatever she...
>> But I trust them. I don't...
>> Okay, so there's no
difference.
>> She doesn't tell me to do
anything.
I'm my own person.
>> And I'm my own person.
Rob doesn't tell me what to do.
>> Well, it sure didn't look
like it.
>> PROBST: So, Parvati, are you
the boss?
>> Of course.
If you ask the Heroes, I'm the
boss.
I'm running a crazy women's
alliance over here.
>> PROBST: Parvati, what about
Courtney is not trustworthy?
>> For me, it's not about
trustworthiness.
It's about alliances.
I mean, in the beginning of this
game, there was a strong
division-- Boston Rob's girls
versus Russell's girls-- and
Rob's gone.
>> I'll tell you what trust will
do.
We had a group of ten.
We had three people that really
trust each other-- me, Parvati
and Danielle-- and we're still
sitting here.
That's what trust can do for
you.
If you really believe it, and if
it's really true, you can make
it all the way to the end in
this game.
>> PROBST: Courtney, that ring
true to you?
>> Yeah, there's a tight
alliance that formed, and you
can't hate on the three of them.
But you know, I stuck with Rob
when I knew he was going to go,
and so that was, like, the
beginning of the end for me and
Sandra's side, which Jerri was a
part of and Coach was a part of,
too, in the beginning and then
it all went...
>> No, I never asked to be a
part of that group, not once,
so...
>> You didn't vote for Parvati?
>> I was never in anybody's
alliance, is my point...
>> All right, well you voted
against the alliance you're a
part of now, but you flipped
just in time to save your butt,
so awesome for you.
I didn't flip quick enough, I
guess, and so, that's why me and
Sandra are in trouble.
>> PROBST: Well, the stakes are
clearly high.
Now, it's time to make your
decision.
It is time to vote.
Sandra, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Jerri.
Courtney.
One vote-- Jerri, one vote--
That's three votes-- Courtney,
one vote-- Jerri.
Tenth person voted out and the
second member of our jury--
Courtney.
That's four. That's enough.
You need to bring me your
torch.
Courtney, the tribe has spoken.
>> Good luck, bitches.
See you later.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: Time for you to go.
>> Bye, Courtney.
>> Bye.
>> PROBST: Well, time will tell
if you made the right vote
tonight, but here's one thing
for sure-- we are now even.
Five Villains, five Heroes.
One other note-- congratulations
to Parvati.
Tomorrow, you will join Amanda
as the only people to have
played 100 days in the game of
Survivor.
>> Thank you, Jeff.
>> PROBST: Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
>> This ought to be interesting.
>> PROBST: Five Heroes and Five
Villains...
>> PROBST: ...will collide.
This is where I stand.
>> They think they have the game
right now.
>> Whatever Russell says, he's
lying if he says that the women
are running the show.
>> This is where the game gets
crazy.
>> I have to say that I am very
proud of myself.
This is pretty good for the
little skinny chick to get all
the way to the jury.
Good for me.
It's actually one of my Survivor
dreams to be on the jury and get
all pretty and make all the
bitches jealous as they sit
there in their dirty rags.
I've been really lucky in both
my Survivor experiences, and
there's nobody I intensely hate.
So, good luck everybody.