>> JEFF PROBST: Last week, 20
seasons of Survivor led up to
our most epic battle yet.
Rob Mariano, one of the game's
ultimate strategists, and also
one of the biggest double
dealers, had recreated himself
as a hero.
>> A lot has happened with me
personally in my life in the
six years since I've played
this game.
I'm learning compromise and
patience.
>> PROBST: He led his tribe of
Villains by being a straight
shooter and working hard.
>> I'm in awe of Rob.
You are the man.
And it's like, when you talk,
I'm literally hanging on
every word.
>> I appreciate it.
>> PROBST: Because of his
efforts, the tribe flourished.
Rob jumps down on the final
piece!
Villains win immunity!
But he made an enemy of Russell.
>> Watch your back, man.
>> Yeah, well, same thing for
you, man.
>> PROBST: Who used lies,
intimidation and chaos to
further his own self-interest.
>> I'm that good, where I can
bring people together in this
game for my good.
>> PROBST: So Rob's leadership
was short-lived.
>> My idea of trust and loyalty
is different from Russell's.
>> PROBST: Motivated by
jealousy, Russell used his
power of persuasion and
gathered enough votes to
eliminate his adversary.
Rob.
The loss of Rob has given the
Heroes a chance at a comeback.
Now, they're down only two
members.
(shrieks happily)
And they've even discovered a
clue to a hidden immunity idol.
>> We're going to look for it
together.
>> PROBST: But the bigger
question: how will losing
Rob's leadership and challenge
dominance impact the Villain
tribe?
>> The waters are so muddy
right now.
I mean, we were in the best
position possible.
>> PROBST: Coach, Courtney and
Sandra refused to vote for Rob,
and now they're trapped in a
tribe controlled by Russell,
whose ego may have just put the
Villains in a hole they can't
get out of.
(laughs)
>> Boston Rob was after me.
You know what?
I just won.
Big-time Boston Rob, the super
All-Star-- he ain't nothing on
me.
>> It's, like, game on now, huh?
>> I'm controlling this game.
I'll take care of all of them,
one at a time.
This is Russell Hantz.
If you ain't with me, you're
against me.
>> It's fun.
>> So much fun.
>> I only like doing it to
people that deserve it.
>> Me, too.
(women laughing)
>> I did not want Boston Rob
out.
We screwed up the whole tribe.
Ridiculous that they're cowards
and they want to vote out
Boston Rob, because Russell is a
bully.
No more, no less.
He's a bully.
>> I mean, I didn't want to
vote off Rob this early, either.
I really didn't.
And the more I thought about
it, the more I was really upset
about it.
I miss him already.
>> I wasn't quick to get rid of
him.
What are you talking about?
>> I feel like Jerri made a big
mistake in aligning with
Russell.
Now I'm forced to go that
direction, and I feel at this
point that it's an alliance
based on lies.
Are we going to the final five
with them or are we going to
try to make a play?
>> I say we just see what
happens at the merge.
>> The Villains are in the
crapper.
I don't think we'll win another
challenge.
We're done.
We're toast.
Pray for the merge.
(theme song playing)
>> Beautiful.
How high up do you want
to go?
>> I say we bring it up pretty
high.
>> Where's J.T.?
>> I don't know.
>> The Hero tribe has plans to
look for the hidden immunity
idol as a group, but the best
thing for me is to make sure I
know where it's at.
This is Survivor, and you
don't know what these other
people are thinking around here.
The clue said that the idol's
in the creek or something.
So I'm just going to swing by
there and take a gander.
Perfect.
I'm going to get the hell out
of here while I still can.
>> You just found it now?
Oh, my God.
>> Let's get out of here.
Immediately after I found it, I
was like, you know what?
I better get out of here, 'cause
I wasn't sure if I was going to
tell anyone.
And before I could even move,
Amanda walked up, so I was like,
well, I'll show her.
>> You found it?
>> I just found it.
Then, immediately, Candice
walked up, so I was like, you
know what, if I come clean, our
tribe will come together.
No one is going to vote me out,
because I have it.
>> Right behind that tree.
(laughs)
I walked up, back up my alone
walk...
>> Yeah.
>> Five minutes.
>> Can I see it?
>> Yeah.
The first one of us that needs
this after the merge, we'll use
it.
>> It's a beautiful thing.
>> Yep.
>> And we're taking them down
with it.
>> Nice.
>> Beautiful.
>> Colby!
>> Sweet!
Nice work, brother.
>> You want some coconut?
>> I'm good.
>> Good thing you walked up.
How close was that?
J.T. found the hidden immunity
idol, which is not so great in
my book, because J.T. is the
slimiest guy out here.
He's running the tribe.
He's got a little best friend
interest with everybody.
And every vote, he's been the
one that's going back and forth,
and everybody's coming to him,
trying to figure out which way
is J.T. going to go.
And nobody calls him out.
I'm afraid to ever say anything
about J.T., because he's, like,
the golden boy, you know.
He's always right about
everything.
Like, he's always in with
everybody.
>> Yeah.
>> Right?
Isn't he in with you?
>> Is he in with you?
>> Isn't he in with Rupert?
Isn't he in with Colby?
>> It would be in Amanda's best
interest to work with me to get
rid of him and the idol or get
rid of the idol.
Either way.
J.T.'s dangerous.
>> I know.
>> We're all going to die.
>> No, we're not.
>> Yeah, we will.
>> No, we won't.
>> You can't not eat for that
long.
>> Yeah, you can.
It's unbelievable.
We're literally starving out
here.
And I'm worried.
I mean, people are shutting
down, and you can see it.
I mean, we're already on our
heels 'cause we're losing.
The time for exigency has
exited.
It is do-or-die out here.
>> "Now for a challenge that's
good clean fun-- no oil, no mud,
no brawling.
It's not who strikes first but
who strikes the most.
Your best meal yet is calling."
>> It sounds like an individual
type thing.
>> Yeah, it does.
>> Yeah, I mean, it doesn't say
anything about tribe.
"Your best meal yet is calling."
Sounds like a merge to me.
Today, the Villains are all
hoping that it's a merge.
It's a challenge of good, clean
fun, and our best meal yet is
calling, so I'm happy about
that.
I think we should take it.
>> I think we should take
everything.
>> Just in case we don't come
back.
I'm hoping and praying that it's
a merge.
And we don't know where
we're going to end up, so we
definitely want to get all of
our stuff together and take the
tools, the tarp, all of our
belongings, because we could
end up somewhere else.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
>> Oh... my God!
>> Wow!
>> Oh, look, pizza, guys.
>> Oh!
>> PROBST: Heroes getting your
first look at the new Villain
tribe.
Boston Rob voted out at the
last Tribal Council.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Wow!
>> Looks like we're, uh,
merging.
>> PROBST: So, Rupert, shocked
that Boston Rob is gone?
>> It sure looks like they got
a woman's alliance.
>> PROBST: Time will tell.
>> When I found out that the
Hero tribe thinks this is an
all-girl alliance, I thought
they're making a huge mistake,
because there's no girl
alliance over here.
Rob got voted out last night
because of me.
But now, if we merge, the Hero
tribe-- they'll let me know
whoever they're voting for if
they think I'm the one that
flop.
Why wouldn't I flop if I'm in
trouble?
Like... help.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: Villains, you
brought, clearly, your entire
camp.
Talk to me, Russell.
>> I'm sure everybody has the
merge in mind.
And if there is a merge, we're
prepared, they're not.
>> The first thought I had when
we saw them walk in with
toolbox in hand was, okay, go
back through your mind.
You read the same clue they
did, what did I not pick up
on?
>> PROBST: It's true, you have
survived 18 days out here.
No small feat.
You've survived
eight Tribal Councils.
Very tough to do.
And it does seem that you
deserve a bit of a break.
As you have all seen behind
you...
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: ...a very nice feast.
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: You'll all have
an opportunity to
enjoy this feast.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh, wait. What?!
>> Wait a minute, wait a minute!
What's, what's the rub?
>> PROBST: Before we move any
further, let me answer the
question on everybody's mind.
Everybody drop
your...
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: ...expectations.
(all groan)
>> Evil!
>> PROBST: We are not merging.
>> Wah-wah-wah. Mean.
>> Try and take it off.
>> PROBST: This is a reward
challenge.
Both tribes will have an
equal opportunity to win it.
You win it, you eat.
Losers go back to camp,
and if it is the Villains,
you will clearly be
putting your shelter back
together.
>> That's right.
>> PROBST: Here's how it works:
today's challenge, you're gonna
do a little Survivor bowling.
It's very simple.
You will square off
against a tribe member from
the other tribe.
Your goal: roll
the ball down the lane, knock
over as many pins as you can.
You get two rolls.
Whoever knocks over the most
pins scores a point for
their tribe.
First tribe to score
three points wins reward.
Villains, you have two
extra members, sitting two
people out.
Cannot sit out the same two
people in back-to-back
challenges.
Who are you gonna sit out?
>> Didn't you guys say that you
were good at bowling?
>> Yeah.
>> Sandra, do you want to bowl?
>> This isn't open...
>> PROBST: Give me an answer.
>> Do you like to bowl?
Are you good at bowling?
>> Yeah, but think about it
who we have to sit out
in the next challenge.
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Coach, who's
sitting out?
>> Sandra and Courtney.
>> PROBST: Sandra and Courtney
are sitting out.
You two take a
spot on the bench.
Everybody else,
I'll give you a minute to
figure out your order, and we'll
get started.
All right, here we go.
First round.
Parvati for the Villains
taking on Rupert for the Heroes.
Parvati, give it a go.
>> Gutter ball, gutter ball.
All right!
>> PROBST: Gutter ball
for the Villains.
Opens the door for Rupert.
>> That a boy, Rupe.
>> PROBST: Rupert
knocks over three.
>> That a way, Rupe.
>> All right, Parvati,
you got it.
>> PROBST: Parvati, you have
to pick up at least three.
>> Gutter ball,
gutter ball, yes.
>> PROBST: Parvati,
another gutter ball.
Rupert doesn't even have
to roll.
Heroes win the
first point and lead 1-zip.
Next round, J.T.
for the Heroes, taking on
Danielle for the Villains.
J.T., you're up.
Right down the middle.
>> Beautiful!
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: Big hit by J.T.,
knocking over six pins on his
first roll.
>> PROBST: Danielle has good
form, but results in another
gutter ball for the Villains.
J.T. with his second shot.
Just misses.
>> Oh, close! It's okay.
>> PROBST: Danielle, you have to
knock over at least six pins.
>> Come on, Danielle.
>> You got it, Danielle.
>> Let's go, Danielle.
>> PROBST: That's not gonna
do it.
Danielle throws a gutter ball.
Heroes now lead it two-zip.
We're playing to three.
Next round, Russell for the
Villains, taking on Colby for
the Heroes.
Russell is the last chance
or the Villains to
stay in this challenge.
Russell takes a
little baby toss, and it
results in an absolute goose
egg for the Villains.
Colby with his
first shot for the Heroes.
>> Bounce, baby!
>> PROBST: Colby bounces his
down the middle, also results
in a gutter ball.
We are zip-zip.
>> Go, Russell.
>> Good shot.
>> Yeah!
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Russell knocks
over five pins for the
Villains, putting a lot of
pressure on Colby.
Gotta pick up at least five.
Colby throws, and
knocks over one.
(Colby blows raspberry)
Villains are on the board.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Heroes lead it 2-1.
Playing to three.
Next round.
Coach from the Villains
taking on Amanda from
the Heroes.
Big feast just sitting over
there waiting on ya.
Amanda could win
it for the Heroes.
Coach could tie it up.
Coach rolls first.
Nice roll by Coach knocking over
five pins.
Amanda now up for the Heroes.
Amanda knocks over five pins.
Two good first rolls.
We're tied 5-5.
Coach, you're up.
Coach with his second roll...
knocks over one more,
putting the pressure on Amanda.
Amanda, to win this,
you need just knock down
two pins.
Good roll.
Amanda knocks over two pins
just barely!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: Heroes win their
third-straight challenge
in a row.
>> Good bowling, Coach.
>> PROBST: Villains, got nothing
for you.
Grab all your stuff.
Head back to whatever
is left of your camp.
All right, Heroes,
you earned it.
Enjoy your feast.
>> Thank you, Jeff!
>> All right!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Come on in, guys!
>> Yay!
>> This is so awesome!
>> Shall we?
>> Cheers!
>> Good job, you guys.
>> Mmm...
>> You guys, we kicked ass
today.
I love all y'all.
Best team on Survivor
right here.
>> The fantastic five.
>> Yay!
>> I mean, I don't want
to jinx us here, but
we're on a little bit of a roll.
But the Villains still have
the numbers.
So, in our minds,
we're still catching up.
We don't want to
get overconfident.
We just want to keep it going.
>> This is good.
>> Oh, God, this is good.
>> I was not ready to merge yet.
>> No, not yet.
We need to knock
two more of them out.
>> How about Boston rob?
(Rupert laughs)
>> Crazy.
>> Insane voting him out!
>> It was a bold move.
>> It was a silly move.
>> The moment Boston Rob
left the game, I knew
the guys were not in control
because he was their
best competitor.
So it's obvious; there's an
all-woman's alliance over there.
>> The girls are gonna
expect you guys to jump
in their girl alliance, but
I know...
>> We would be the first
ones to find out who
they're voting for.
>> That's the whole thing.
>> Now Coach and Russell
are on the outs over there.
They're sitting ducks.
If we merge right now,
we've got them on our side
in a heartbeat, you know?
So right now, I think we stick
to our plan and just
keep dominating.
We're still losing.
We got 'em on the hills.
>> I love you all.
>> I love you, too.
>> It's a family, guys.
>> Hear, hear.
>> To the fantastic five.
>> Every single person on this
team is an idiot.
I just, I'm furious.
This whole stupid thing,
packing up the whole camp,
just assuming there was
gonna be a merge.
Are you kidding me?
You know, voting off Rob
was a big mistake.
He would have made sure
that Sandra and Courtney
did not sit out today, that
they played, and they we had
strong people in the immunity
challenge.
>> We already made that mistake
once and we just let it
happen again.
I looked at both of them
of them and I said, "You guys,
can you do this?"
And they're, like, "Um,
I don't know."
>> You said, you said, no,
you said, "I don't know."
>> It's, like, so now it's me
and Courtney's fault that you
guys lost?
>> No, no, it's not.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying why did this stupid
mistake get made again that we
made the last time?
>> He's the one
that said Sandra and Courtney.
>> I know.
>> So then me and Courtney
are looking like, "Okay, so then
we'll both have to compete in
the immunity challenge.
That's a big mistake.
>> Yeah, I said the same thing,
but it was Coach.
You said, "I really want
pizza."
And I said, "We don't need
pizza.
We need an immunity.
>> We need to eat
and we need to win.
Sandra and Courtney.
Why are you
blaming me and Courtney?
>> I'm not blaming you
and Courtney.
>> Why? We didn't even
do anything.
>> All I'm saying is that
if even once, you guys
were like, "Hell, yeah,
"put me in there!
I want to go."
>> So, in essence,
the reason we lost today was
because he and Courtney sat out.
>> Again, no, that's not
what it has to do with, again.
>> I just don't understand.
The minute we get back to camp,
and you guys don't have a meal,
all of a sudden, it's me
and Courtney.
The worst tribe ever put
together is the Villains tribe.
I should not even be here.
I should be with the Heroes
'cause I can't stand Jerri.
I hate Coach, I hate Danielle.
I hate Russell even more.
So any of those--
I'm not going to pick one above
the other 'cause I equally hate
them all.
>> Tyson's gone,
Rob's gone, and now we're the
ones on the outs.
And it's 5-2.
Russell's the kind of
person where if he finds out
somebody's gunning for him,
he'll take them out.
if one of us is going next..
I'll be like, "Hey, Russell.
Coach wants you gone."
And I bet you Russell
will believe me and get
rid of Coach, and me and
Courtney will be saved again.
I'm going to work
my magic and we're both going
to be here on day 22 and day 23.
I didn't want to play
this game without Tyson.
I didn't want to play this
game without Boston Rob.
And it's like all that's
out the window.
>> I guess that maybe
you feel guilty or something,
but I know I'm the next one
to go.
And what else is there to say,
you know?
It's based on
Russell's idea of what he wants
his Survivor to be like, and
everyone's going along with it
out of, like, fear or something.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh.
>> But it don't
matter what she says.
I will tell them
this is how we're voting.
And that's how it's going to be.
That simple.
>> But at the same time, I heard
Coach was saying that he made a
mistake and he wished he could
go back.
>> What mistake?
>> Him letting Rob go home.
That he should have never made
the choice that he made, and
that he's sorry.
That's what he told her.
And that he wanted to get rid
of you.
So, I don't know about
your homeboy.
>> Oh, he ain't my homeboy.
I don't trust him.
Obviously, you can't trust him.
Because of that right there.
He's going behind my back,
saying stuff like that.
You know... you know, he's...
he's digging his own grave, just
like Rob did.
>> I told Russell that Coach was
talking about voting for him,
and Russell's so stupid, he ate
that crap up.
I'm telling you, he's like, "Oh,
my God, I can't trust him."
And the sooner he goes,
the better.
So, Russell, you don't know how
to play this game.
Yeah, he's done good so far,
but with me, he don't know what
he got himself into.
>> He's going to flip.
He's mad at me for getting rid
of Rob, and now he's trying to
stab me in the back.
>> Who does he think he is?
>> And you know the beautiful
thing about all this?
If he goes, there's one guy
left, and there's no doubt in
their minds what's going on.
>> That there's a girl alliance.
>> Once we merge, they ain't
going to talk to one of
the girls.
They're going to be scared to
death to, but they're surely
going to come straight to me.
>> Perfect.
>> It's all falling together
perfectly.
Mmm.
>> You've done that before.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Rupert?
Take back immunity.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
be belted together in pairs.
You'll race through the mud,
going under and over a series of
obstacles to retrieve a flag.
You'll then race back.
First pair back with their flag
scores a point for their tribe.
First tribe to score two points
wins immunity, is safe once
again from Tribal Council.
Losers, you know what's
happening.
Somebody voted out of
your tribe.
Because we have odd numbers, one
of the matchups will be a
one-on-one showdown.
Villains, you have two
extra members.
Courtney and Sandra sat out
last time.
That means you are in this time.
Who's going to sit out for
the Villains?
>> Why don't you and Danielle
sit out and I'll play.
>> PROBST: Jerri and Danielle
sitting out.
All right.
Sit-outs, take a spot over here.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, we have our
first matchup.
It's Russell and Sandra taking
on Amanda and Candice.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
>> Here we go.
Here we go, team.
>> PROBST: Go!
>> Come on, Amanda!
Let's go, Candice!
>> PROBST: Amanda and Candice
under the obstacle first.
Russell and Sandra right behind.
Sandra slow through that
first obstacle.
Carrying a lot of mud, you
weigh a lot more.
Amanda and Candice over for
the Heroes.
We're neck and neck at the
second obstacle.
>> Down, down!
>> Dig, dig, dig!
>> Grab, grab, grab!
>> Let's go, let's go!
>> PROBST: Amanda and Candice
have the flag for the Heroes.
Russell and Sandra very slow
under that third obstacle.
Sandra really struggling.
>> Come on, Sandra!
>> PROBST: Amanda and Candice
taking their time.
No rush at all.
You can see the look on
Russell's face.
It says it all-- absolute
frustration-- as Amanda and
Candice continue further down
on the course.
>> Beautiful.
>> PROBST: Amanda and Candice
score for the Heroes.
Sandra is stuck.
Trying to back out of that
challenge now.
Heroes lead one-zip.
Time for a showdown.
Coach taking on Rupert
one-on-one.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Go, Dragon Slayer!
>> Go, Rupe!
>> PROBST: Both men go
head first.
Coach is out of the gate first
for the Villains.
Coach over the second obstacle
first for the Villains.
Coach flying through
this course.
>> That a way, Rupe!
>> PROBST: Rupert right on
his tail.
Rupert now picks up some ground.
Both men have their flags.
Rupert now in the lead for
the Heroes.
Rupert flies over that
second obstacle.
It's Rupert and Coach
neck and neck.
It's going to be a race to
the finish.
Coach wins for the Villains!
We are tied one-one.
All right, here we go.
The final round.
Parvati and Courtney taking on
J.T. and Colby.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, you guys.
Let's go, Courtney.
J.T. and Colby dive head first.
Parvati and Courtney very slow
under that first obstacle.
>> Come on, you guys.
You guys, you got it!
>> Courtney, let's go!
Pick it up, girls!
Let's go!
>> PROBST: Courtney and Parvati
falling behind.
J.T. and Colby head first again.
>> Come on, you guys!
You got it!
>> PROBST: J.T. and Colby have
the flag.
They're heading back.
Parvati and Courtney are not
even at their flag yet.
Heroes are almost at the
end now.
This is not even close.
J.T. and Colby score for
the Heroes.
Heroes win immunity!
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
Nice work!
>> Oh, my God!
>> PROBST: You all right,
Courtney?
>> She hurt her ankle.
>> PROBST: See if you can make
it on your own.
If not, we'll get medical
in there.
Heroes, congratulations
once again.
No Tribal Council for
the Heroes.
The new five stays intact.
Villains, four straight
challenges in a row.
Another trip to Tribal Council.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I'll see you tonight at Tribal.
>> I want Courtney gone.
I am a competitor.
I hate losing.
This is not fair to keep people
in the game that don't have any
physical ability at all.
And they're actually making
us lose.
>> I'm just going to jump in.
>> Me, too.
>> Whoo!
>> Another day in the dirt.
>> What a challenge.
It was the muddiest one yet.
You know how I look at it?
It's like going to a spa.
>> Oh, you bruised your
shoulder, too, right here.
>> Right there.
>> Everybody's down.
Everybody's hurting.
Everybody's nauseous.
(inhales deeply)
And the Dragon Slayer is just
coming into his own.
I feel full of energy, and it's
time for me to shine.
Off into the horizon.
But, anyways, we're going to
Tribal, and part of me says I
ought to just get rid of
Russell tonight.
He's knocked out both of my best
friends in this game.
But the way we're losing
challenges, to keep one of the
weaker girls and get rid of
Russell-- it might be a mistake.
So, I guess I'm going to stay
with the forced five alliance
and vote out Courtney, who is
the weakest link.
(thunder rumbling)
Any, uh, funny stuff going on?
>> Everything's still the same
as far as I'm concerned.
>> Yeah.
>> I get my mind set on one
thing, and I do it.
If I can't trust them, got to
get rid of them.
Coach-- Sandra said he wants me
gone now.
I have the power in this game.
I send home who I want to
send home.
I've already talked to Parvati,
and she's really on board with
voting for Coach.
And Sandra and Courtney, I think
they'll put Coach's name down
for sure.
So the big Coach, the Coach Man,
the Dragon Slayer, he's going
home tonight.
>> Honestly, if we don't merge,
we're screwed.
They're going to... they're just
going to... we'll be done.
>> That's what's going to
happen anyway.
We're losing every single
one anyway.
>> No, we're not.
We have a chance if we
have Coach.
>> Look what we're doing
with Coach.
We're getting dominated.
>> Because of Courtney
and Sandra.
>> That's a stupid move.
I don't know how you're
thinking right now.
I don't know how you're playing
the game.
We keep Coach and we lose the
next one, you'll make sure your
butt's on the line for that.
You... you would put your butt
on the line...
>> I'm just saying we have a
better shot.
>> I'm not... you are freaking
out right now.
Chill out.
>> You ain't making any sense.
>> Yes, I am!
It's stupid to let him go.
I don't think it's...
>> I just told you, I don't
agree with it.
>> You're not listening to me!
>> I ain't going to ... talk
to you no more.
>> I'm ... giving you
suggestions.
>> Just calm down!
>> I'm looking at it in
different ways.
You're just like...
>> Geez!
>> Whatever, Russell.
(groans)
I think it's really stupid
to get rid of another
strong player.
I mean, Courtney and Sandra
can't do anything in
the challenge.
They've proved that to us a
million times over.
I mean, Courtney was just
pathetic.
And I think we have a shot at
least with Coach.
So, I mean, I threw that out
there, and Russell freaked out
and screamed at me because he's
just so in control of this game,
and everything has to go the
way he wants it to go.
So, I mean, as of right now, I'm
up in the air.
I got to really think about what
I want to do.
>> Because she's such a
competitor.
You know what I'm saying?
She was like, "I'm done
suggesting things."
So I think she must have
suggested something to Russell.
>> If my plan to vote out Coach
doesn't work, I think Courtney
is going home.
I put a bug in Russell's ear
that Coach wants to get rid of
him.
But Russell was talking to
Danielle a few minutes ago.
And the conversation-- it looked
like it was going back and
forth.
So I don't know.
All I can do is hope that Coach
is going to go home, and that's
it.
>> Do you know where the saw is?
The one that we open coconuts
with?
>> I think Danielle might be
right.
We might need to keep him one
more time.
We can always take him out, any
time we want.
I think we should vote Courtney.
>> It's absurd.
First, Russell wants to vote
off Coach.
And then, all of a sudden, he
wants to vote Courtney.
Jeez!
This tribe cannot get its act
together.
That's a problem.
You know, we can't make a
decision as a cohesive unit to
save our lives.
>> We couldn't be no cooler.
>> Hopefully, we all come
together and vote out the
dragon slayer.
But who knows?
They might still get together
and, say, vote off the weakest
and target me and vote me out.
You never know what's going to
happen between now and when the
sun goes down.
>> PROBST: Let's start tonight's
Tribal Council by going back
to the last two Tribal Councils.
Tyson and Rob-- the result:
four straight losses with no
end in sight.
Danielle, any second thoughts
about voting out Tyson and Rob?
>> This decision was made.
We thought it would be smarter,
because they were such big
threats.
So, it is what it is, Jeff.
We thought what we did was the
right thing to do.
>> PROBST: But in a physical
challenge, the only person who
won a point today was Coach.
>> Ah.
>> PROBST: And if given the
choice of Tyson or Boston Rob
over, say, Courtney, I think 99
out of 100 people would probably
pick Tyson or Boston Rob-- no
disrespect.
>> Thank you, Jeffrey.
>> PROBST: Courtney, you've sat
out a majority of the
challenges.
>> That's what the team wanted
to do.
I don't have a big ego that has
to go and run and play in every
single thing.
I wasn't a part of the decision
to vote out Tyson or Rob, so
I'm sad that they're both gone.
But insulting me is not going
to bring them back.
>> PROBST: It's not meant as an
insult.
It's meant as just one person's
observation.
Boston Rob was dominating.
>> I agree with you.
>> PROBST: But Danielle just
told me that's why you voted
him out.
>> I didn't vote him out of our
tribe.
The tribe voted him out, because
he was not in the dominating
alliance.
>> PROBST: Coach, what do you
think the take is on this tribe
from the outside looking in?
>> I personally feel like
people are probably laughing at
us right now and saying that we
deserve it.
Like, today, when we were
getting ready for the
challenge, I was trying to
energize people and I was, like,
saying, "All right, come on,
guys, let's do it."
And I had comments like, "Well,
I'm gonna do my best."
>> PROBST: Courtney, you're not
having any of that.
>> When, you know, it's a reward
challenge, it was Coach saying,
"Well, I want to eat, so A
squad on."
And then, "I don't care about
the immunity challenge, 'cause
we'll put the two weak people in
there."
And then, obviously, it will
be one of the us going home.
>> So what I hear from you is
that the reason why our morale
is down is because of me.
Is that what I'm hearing?
>> PROBST: That's what I heard.
>> This is crazy.
I don't sit there and make
unilateral decisions and say,
"By the way, Courtney and
Sandra, you guys should sit out
every challenge."
I've never said that, because
you don't ever sit out every
challenge out here, so I would
never make a foolhardy statement
like that.
But what we all want as a tribe
is for Courtney to say, "I want
to do that 'cause I can beat
that challenge."
>> Thanks, Dad.
>> He's a Coach.
That's what he does.
He tries to pick people up.
>> I'm not saying that you don't
mean well, it's just the way
that...
>> Well, it certainly sounds
like it when you say that I'm
demoralizing the entire tribe.
Trust me, I am not the person
that is demoralizing this tribe.
In fact, it has absolutely
nothing to do with me.
>> PROBST: Parvati, are you at
all concerned that there may
not be an end to this slide?
And if you ever do merge with
the other tribe, your chances
of winning and getting to the
end go down.
>> I don't think it's that hard
to see that we are definitely
less athletic than them.
So if we continue to do these
physical challenges, they're
going to slaughter us, and we're
going to go, one by one, down
that trail and our torches are
going to get put out by you.
>> PROBST: But we're talking
around the thing that anybody
watching will know to be true,
which is, you guys are making
decisions based on alliances,
the assumption there might be a
merge, and whatever else happens
down the game.
>> Of course!
I mean, everyone's talking about
a merge, and now all of the
sudden, there's not going to be
a merge.
And so it's target the weak, and
I'm, like, poster child for weak
Survivor.
But I'm still here over a bunch
of strong players, so twisted
ankle, skinny chick, whatever,
I'm a determined little bitch,
and I will put up with a lot of
crap to get to the end.
You know?
>> Fist bump.
>> That's right, girl.
(laughs)
>> PROBST: Russell, how is
tonight's vote going to change
this tribe?
>> Well, I think if you can
keep the tribe stronger and
keep the trust in place, that's
what you need to do.
And that's what I'm doing
tonight.
>> PROBST: And with that, it is
time to vote.
Coach, you're up.
>> You're a freaking lunatic.
I'm just glad I don't have to
live with you anymore.
Nice feather in your hair.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Coach.
Coach.
Two votes Coach.
Courtney.
Two votes Coach, one vote
That's two votes Coach, two
votes Courtney.
Courtney.
Three votes Courtney, two votes
Coach.
We're tied.
That's three votes Coach, three
votes Courtney.
One vote left.
Ninth person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs. Villains
and the first member of our
jury...
Coach.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Good luck, guys.
>> PROBST: Coach, tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, after tonight's Tribal
Council, it's clear that the
problem with trust, as I'm
sure Coach would agree, is you
don't know it's gone until it's
too late.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our
next episode.
>> PROBST: In 20 seasons, we've
seen a lot of dumb moves.
>> I'll dive right now if you
take Katie, and I'll give up the
million.
>> I have two idols.
I guess I should have played
them.
>> It's not the idol.
>> Why do you say that?
>> It's a ... stick!
>> I want to give individual
immunity to Natalie.
>> PROBST: But next time, you
might see one that tops them
all.
>> I get a chance to talk to
Russell, I give him the hidden
immunity idol.
>> I never thought that I would
be going out so soon.
I had so much that I wanted to
accomplish and so much that I
wanted to prove and redeem.
I'm exhausted, and still in a
state of shock.
But I am probably more pissed
off than I've been in a number
of years.
And, you know, I really am not a
very vindictive person, but I
hope they get wiped off the
face of the map.