>> JEFF PROBST: Previously,
on...
J.T. and Boston Rob go at
it hard.
...Survivor:
Coach takes a hard hit.
By day 12, it was all-out war
between the Heroes and the
Villains...
Whoa!
Stop, stop!
...and James was the latest
casualty.
But the biggest battle was back
at the Villains' camp.
Parvati was fighting for her
life.
>> Move your arms like this.
>> Parvati is the most
dangerous player on our tribe.
>> PROBST: Meanwhile, Russell
and Rob battled it out for
tribal supremacy.
>> It's personal with me and
Rob.
He thinks he's tough?
May the best man win.
>> PROBST: Russell believed he
was in an alliance with
Danielle and Parvati, and he had
the hidden immunity idol.
Rob believed he was aligned
with everyone else.
Rob jumps down on the final
piece!
Villains win immunity!
But when Rob led the Villains
to yet another victory, his
battle with Russell was
postponed.
Villains, congratulations.
While the Heroes were marching
into another vote, James'
injury made him a liability, and
Candice considered voting with
the outsiders, Tom and Colby,
to take him out.
>> You can't lug around dead
weight-- and James is a lot of
dead weight.
>> PROBST: But at Tribal Council
she played it safe and voted
with the majority to take out
Tom...
The tribe has spoken.
...making Colby the odd man out
in a tribe going nowhere fast.
15 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Really?
>> At Tribal tonight, Tom went
home, and, uh... I voted for him
because there's no reason to
throw a vote away and make the
people that are going to be
coming home tonight mad at me.
>> Everyone's annoyed with
Candice.
>> In reality, nobody trusts
her.
She was gunning for James.
I'm so sick of Candice right
now.
So... Candice has to go.
>> I'm just sitting around
and... thinking too much.
I don't want to be at your
throat, I don't want you to be
at my throat.
I've decided to have a
conversation with Rob to make
him think that I'm not after
him, which I am.
I don't care how strong he is.
I don't care who he is.
He's threatening Russell Hantz--
when you do that, you go.
>> A lot of people are mad,
though, that you went looking
for that idol... because we all
said nobody's gonna look for it,
and if they were, then you're
going to be marked.
>> I went looking for it, but...
if I get the next clue, I'll
find it, 'cause I'll go looking
for it again.
>> Russell's going to find out
soon enough that he's out of
his league.
I just did everything I could
to make him as more paranoid as
I could, to see he runs around
like a crazy man.
...but a lot of people are
mad that you went looking for
that idol.
They want your ass off.
He's not playing with the
amateurs anymore.
He's playing with the big boys
now.
I'm just telling you, watch
your back, man.
>> Well, same thing for you,
man. (laughs)
Watch your back.
>> All right.
(theme song playing)
♪ ♪
>> Treemail!
>> Yay!
>> "When things look desperate,
never lose hope.
Never throw in the towel, you
just have to cope.
And never, ever give up, even
when you're at the end of your
rope."
>> Doesn't say whether it's for
reward or immunity.
Treemail was a bit vague this
morning.
We don't know whether it's
reward, immunity or both.
The biggest question to me is,
what does it mean for James?
I would put a whole lot of
money on the fact that there
will be challenges in our
future that James simply will
not be able to do...
because of his injury.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Villains getting your first
look at the new tribe of Heroes.
Tom voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> (whispers): James is still
there.
>> PROBST: Danielle...
surprised at this vote?
>> Yes, definitely.
We for sure thought James would
be gone, but he must have a
strong alliance on the other
side.
>> PROBST: All right, you guys
ready to get to today's
challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Sandra?
(Sandra chuckles)
I'll take it back.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
Today it's a little different.
Today you'll be competing as
individuals... against your own
tribe, seeking to win...
individual immunity, which will
keep you safe at tonight's
Tribal Council-- because tonight
both tribes are going to Tribal
Council.
>> (whispers): Wow!
>> PROBST: Both tribes are
voting somebody out.
This is your chance to make
sure it is not you.
So both tribes will run this
challenge separately.
Here's how it works.
Each person will be attached to
a long rope that is threaded
through a series of obstacles.
You'll climb over, crawl under,
maneuver around those obstacles
as you make your way to the
finish.
First person to the finish wins
individual immunity, is safe at
Tribal Council.
After both tribes have run this
challenge, the two winners--
one from each tribe-- will then
square off in a showdown.
The winner of that challenge
wins for their tribe hot dogs,
fixin's, soft drinks, which you
will enjoy tonight as you
listen in on the other tribe's
Tribal Council.
So you not only win food, you
get insight into the dynamics
of the other tribe.
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: A lot at stake.
One thing of note.
Coach, J.T. and Tyson all
competed in this challenge in
their season.
J.T. and Tyson went on to the
final; Tyson ultimately won
this challenge.
All right, we'll rock, paper,
scissor to see who goes first.
We'll get started.
Villains won the rock, paper,
scissor.
They want the Heroes to go
first.
Fighting for individual
immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You got to follow the rope
through the course.
Your body has to go wherever
that rope goes.
You're going to have to throw
yourself through this course if
you want a shot at winning.
James, even with a bad knee, is
fighting to stay in this.
>> Man!
>> Wow.
>> PROBST: Definitely affecting
his mobility, but not his
spirit.
Amanda now in the lead.
Candice right there in it.
There are going to be a lot of
scrapes, bumps, bruises when
this is over.
James now in the lead in this
challenge.
Who would have ever predicted
this?
>> Amazing!
>> PROBST: It is J.T., Candice,
Rupert and James.
Colby still stuck in the middle.
Hung up.
Amanda falling behind.
Candice through the first
section before anybody else!
J.T. now through the first
section.
It's J.T. and Candice!
Individual immunity on the line.
Only way to make sure you're
safe tonight is to win this.
Amanda now in the second
section.
Rupert now in the second
Candice wins individual
immunity!
>> Candice is the only thing
stopping Colby from going home
next, and when she won immunity
he had to be thinking, "You know
what?
I just done me in."
>> PROBST: Candice,
congratulations.
Candice safe at tonight's
Tribal Council.
I'll take a hug.
Everybody else unbelt, take
your spots on the bench,
Villains, we'll get you hooked
up.
Nice work.
All right, next round.
Villains now fighting for
individual immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
See if they learned anything by
watching the Heroes do it first.
Rob and Tyson throwing
themselves through this
challenge.
Russell squirming through this
fairly quickly.
Danielle trying to make a go of
it.
Parvati's right there in it.
Sandra stuck early.
Jerri struggling to get through.
You cannot be timid in this
challenge.
It will not work.
Right off the bat, it is Rob,
Tyson, Russell.
Parvati doing very well.
Sandra making no progress at
all.
Coach launches himself through
this.
Rob's still fighting.
Danielle trying to stay in it.
Parvati is in this.
It's Parvati, Russell, Tyson,
Rob and Coach leading the way
right now.
Boston Rob is through the first
section first.
Tyson now through to the second
section.
It is Boston Rob and Tyson!
Russell now through to the
second section!
Boston Rob, Tyson, Russell
battling for individual
immunity!
Boston Rob is through!
Boston Rob wins immunity!
Rob, congratulations.
Rob is safe at tonight's Tribal
Council for the Villains.
You will now take on Candice in
a showdown.
Unhook.
We'll move on to the showdown.
Here we go.
For the showdown round, we have
Boston Rob from the Villains
taking on Candice from the
Heroes.
Winner of this challenge wins
hot dogs and soft drinks which
you will enjoy tonight while
listening in on the other
tribe's Tribal Council.
Survivors ready.
Go.
>> Go, Boston Rob!
>> You got it, Rob!
>> You got it, Rob! You got it!
>> Focus, Candice!
>> PROBST: We've added a third
level to this challenge, and it
is three times as high.
This is going to be a lot more
difficult than the first round.
>> Come on, Candice!
>> It's all you, Rob.
It's all you.
>> PROBST: Rob with a bit of a
lead, but Candice right on his
tail.
Both Rob and Candice are safe
for the vote tonight.
They're fighting now to win food
for their tribe.
>> Go steady, girl!
>> Go...
>> Keep it going, Rob.
Keep it going.
>> PROBST: Not only do you win
food, you win the right to get
a little insight into the
dynamics of the other tribe.
>> Awesome, Rob!
You look great.
>> Rob, go.
>> PROBST: Rob still with the
lead, but Candice still right
there.
Candice has not lost much
ground.
>> Right on his butt.
You're right on his butt.
>> Come on, Candice!
You're right there.
Don't give up now! Come on!
You're right on him.
>> PROBST: A lot of support from
both tribes.
>> Great job, Rob! Great job.
>> Good job.
You're doing awesome!
>> Really good job.
>> Come on, girl!
This is your honeymoon, girl!
>> Come on, Candice!
You're right there!
>> Your honeymoon night, baby.
Come on, girl.
>> Steady, girl.
>> Stay focused! Yes!
>> Nice!
>> PROBST: Rob getting very
close now.
>> Good job, Rob! Good job, Rob!
>> PROBST: Candice got to pick
it up.
>> Come on, Rob.
You got it, man. It's all you!
>> PROBST: Rob with the last
move.
Rob wins for the Villains!
(cheering and applause)
Villains will eat tonight at
Tribal Council.
>> You get the biggest hot dog!
Yeah.
>> PROBST: All right, so here's
how it's going to work.
Villains, you will go to Tribal
Council first, where Boston Rob
has immunity, cannot be voted
out.
After you've completed your
Tribal Council, we will serve
you hot dogs and soft drinks as
you listen in on the Heroes'
Tribal Council, where Candice
has immunity, cannot be voted
out.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp.
See you both at Tribal Council.
>> I can certainly see where the
tribe might decide I'm the weak
link, so my gut tells me I'll be
going home tonight.
But you never know what your
future holds.
There's so much that's truly up
to those you're playing with.
>> Boston Rob saves the day!
>> Hot dog!
(whooping)
>> Nice work, Rob!
>> Ooh, I beat a girl.
>> I know.
>> I feel so... (roars)
>> Feel like a big man?
Feel like a big man?
>> Job well done.
>> I went into that immunity
challenge thinking, I have to
win this one, and then Rob wins!
And I'm, like, "What?! No!"
Rob having the immunity necklace
puts him in a big position of
power.
>> ...like the other day.
>> Gather round, gather round.
>> What is it?
>> Settled on Parvati,
everybody?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> But we have to make sure they
think it's Russell so that he
plays the idol.
(indistinct chatter)
>> Yeah.
>> Russell sucks me this way,
Tyson and Boston Rob pull me
this way.
You know, I'm totally the
middleman.
I'm smack dab in the center of
two alliances, but we all know
that the dragon slayer is a man
of his word, and when he says
he's going to go this direction,
come hell or high water, that's
who I'm voting for.
I'm voting for Parvati.
>> Let's get her out of here.
I'm over it.
>> Yeah!
>> Just be careful, man, because
I'm telling you, if you really
don't have that idol, you need
to go get it.
>> I don't have it.
>> Well... it's been real.
>> So, you're-you're telling me,
uh...
>> I'm telling you...
>> ...if I don't find the idol,
they'll vote for me tonight?
>> Better to play with me than
against me.
>> Boston Rob tells me, "It's
better to play with me than
against me."
Oh, really?
I believe I'm going to get him
to eat them words.
>> Rob told me it's going to be
me.
I ain't stupid.
They're going to vote Parvati.
But this is what I want to do.
I want to put Tyson's name down.
I want to give you the idol
tonight.
If it doesn't work, I go home,
but I ain't that stupid.
They're trying to blindside you.
>> I needed an A-plus
performance today, and it didn't
happen.
James-- with a brace and all--
managed to beat me.
So, uh, not an impressive
showing, uh, for me today.
Well, I just want to say one
thing, guys.
I know I'm going home tonight,
so there's no... there's no need
for any scrambling or anything
like that.
There's absolutely no hard
feelings on my part.
So let's just have a good,
relaxed afternoon and go on in
there tonight.
I say we give them as little
information as we can.
They're going to be sitting in.
I see the pecking order, and
since Candice had sealed up
immunity, I'm the next one to
go...
Enjoyed it, Rupe.
...so I just said, "Listen,
enjoy our afternoon, head to
Tribal Council tonight."
Um... and I meant it.
...I haven't had a lot of fun,
I mean, I still love this game,
you know?
>> Yeah.
>> Granted, I still think I can
kick your ass.
>> Yeah.
>> But you-you the Great Colby.
>> It wasn't too good today,
that's for sure.
>> Right.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> I hear you.
>> Colby doesn't want to be
here.
There's no way that's the Colby
of old-- one of the baddest
competitors ever.
He has not done anything.
It is bring... almost brought me
to tears.
It's like my Superman sucks.
All his muscles are gone, so
it's very disappointing just to
see a grown man give it up like
that.
>> We're losing our team.
>> I mean, Colby's a good guy.
>> I know.
>> But even with James' leg, my
foot, Colby was last.
>> I'm just... I'm really
shocked that Colby hasn't really
pulled through in anything yet.
You know?
>> I know.
>> But, still, James is hurt.
>> We just got to decide which
one of these is going to suit us
best, because even the...
You know, we all had an alliance
with James, but...
I mean, even James knows, at
this point, we have to win.
>> He's a competitor.
Like, no matter what will
happen, he will give his all
until we win, but we do need
to...
>> But see...
>> But if you're giving your
all, and your knee blows out,
our five has to be the strongest
possible five we could have.
We just have to think, you
know...
>> We have to think who's been
overall best competitor, given
the circumstances right now.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Is what we have to do.
>> Well, how is it going to help
me? I mean...
>> I'm serious.
And you can't steal any more
bananas when we come to camp.
>> Steal any more bananas?
What the ...
>> You're taking bananas when
we come into camp.
>> Everybody eats bananas.
What does that mean?
>> James, you take three of
them.
>> Yeah. I'm...
>> You're pissing people off.
I'm just telling you what's
going on.
James just has to prove that
he's okay.
They're also mad about it,
'cause James, like...
He tends to take a lot of
bananas 'cause he's a big guy.
Like, he's hungry, obviously,
but you know, you're out here
with no food-- it's a big deal
to people.
>> Everybody eats bananas.
It's so...
>> Yeah, but when you get a
banana, you get one for everyone
else.
It's, like, an etiquette.
>> Really?
>> Yes.
>> I mean, I understand.
Whatever.
>> Well, I want to know exactly
what you can do, because if you
show them, you're fine, then
you're fine.
They want you here.
Everyone wants you here.
But if there is a chance that
you're not okay...
>> Well, yeah, there might be,
but, uh... I don't know.
It's up to y'all.
>> Ugh.
>> I'm tired of the talking.
>> What's up?
>> James wants to show us
that he's tough.
>> Oh, God.
Are you serious?
(Rupert chuckles)
>> Who am I racing?
>> If you're racing me, you
already won.
(laughing)
>> We're about to have a race.
He's going to show us that
his leg is okay.
Who do we keep?
James, who is fighting to stay
in the game?
Or Colby, who's ready to walk
out.
>> So I'm running in this
thing, huh?
>> Yeah, I damn sure ain't
running by myself!
(Rupert laughs)
I wanted to prove to y'all that
I'm all right.
Straight up. I mean...
> I don't want to see James go.
James is a hundred percent ally
on my side.
Colby is not.
I'm just gonna say, "Ready, go."
James is a fighter.
Colby is not.
James is power.
Ready?
Colby is not.
Go!
(Rupert grunting)
>> Damn it!
(Rupert laughing)
>> You all right?
>> Damn it!
You got me!
Nah, I'm good. It don't hurt.
>> James is not the kind of
person that's gonna say, "You
know what, I don't think I can
go anymore."
You'll never know it until the
man's in a stretcher that he
was hurt.
>> You still would have beat me.
>> We have to see the big
picture here, look outside of
our friendships and find...
the winning combination.
>> Hey, J.T., would you like a
banana?
(laughing)
♪ ♪
>> Yes, my love?
>> No.
We need to split the vote.
I'm telling you, three of us
vote for Parvati, three of us
vote for Russell.
The three of them are going to
put somebody up, probably you.
I'm telling you, if we vote
three and three and there's a
tie, then there's a revote.
That means either one of those
two are going home.
If he plays the idol, then she's
going home.
If he gives her the idol, he's
Do you understand?
We can't lose.
You can't lose that way.
This other way, it's too risky.
I was just thinking to myself,
you know, Tyson's one of my
allies, and if it were me that
didn't win immunity they'd be
coming after me, and I know
they're coming after him, and I
was just thinking of a way so
that Russell doesn't get the
better of us if he does have the
idol.
>> It's Parvati first option,
Russell second option.
>> Basically, I threw out an
insurance policy, if you will.
There's no way they can backdoor
us with the idol, and we'll all
be safe.
As long as we split our votes,
one of them two goes home.
>> That's it.
>> I think the vote's going to
be pretty... pretty
straightforward tonight.
Rob, myself, Sandra, we're
voting for Russell.
Courtney, Coach and Jerri are
voting for Parvati.
>> Don't sweat it.
I'm telling you.
>> It's not rocket science, but
I don't have immunity, and
anytime I don't have immunity I
feel a little uneasy.
Let me see you for a second,
Tyson.
Let me tell you something.
>> I know.
>> And I just wanted to tell you
I'll do what I have to do to
stay in the game.
There's nothing I can do to
help her.
So I'm going to vote for
Parvati.
>> Yeah, you need to.
>> And then... that'll be it.
She'll go home.
You know, if there's any way I
could've tried to save her, I
would have, but I started
thinking, you know, I got to
play this game for myself.
>> Okay.
When Russell came and told me
that he wanted to vote out
Parvati, I thought it was
actually an excellent
opportunity maybe to swap my
vote to Parvati.
I mean, I want her out.
>> Man, I don't like doing it,
but... got to.
>> I hope there's not a revote,
but I just want to get it over
with and get some hot dog in my
mouth.
>> All right, man.
>> Yep. We're tight, dude.
>> You know, the smartest thing
for them to do is make it a
three-way tie.
That would force the idol.
Then they can play however they
want to play on the second vote.
That would be a genius move.
I don't know they're that smart.
I don't know if it would be the
right thing giving Parvati the
idol.
It's just... this is a really
tough decision here.
Way worse than last time.
It's...
it is really bad.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Jerri, going all the
way back to season two, what is
one significant way Survivor's
changed?
>> It's, like, you get out here
and it's game on.
Like, trying to create
alliances, that sort of thing,
right from the get-go, and it
seems like the typical survival
things, now they're not as
important.
>> PROBST: Rob, what's another
element that's different now
that we didn't have back in
season four?
>> Hidden immunity idols.
That puts a whole other twist
in the game.
I mean, you can use it to
protect yourself, to protect
somebody else.
You don't know whether somebody
has it or not.
>> We all know who has it.
Russell, if you don't have it
and you didn't find it, you'd
best look for it.
Point-blank.
>> PROBST: So, Russell, there's
at least one person in here
who's certain you have it, and
if you don't, that makes it
tough for you.
>> Not really.
I mean, if you ain't got it,
you can't play it.
So it don't make it too tough
for me.
>> PROBST: Tyson, do you think
it's better if you do have the
idol, or it's something you
really want nothing to do with
it?
>> Well, I guess it can help
you in some instances, but when
the numbers are this big still,
it's... it's not gonna be that
beneficial.
>> PROBST: Parvati, as a tribe,
you guys have done very well.
But still, there have to be
things about each person on
this tribe that you're a little
suspect of, shady about.
What's the take on Tyson?
>> Tyson's a threat, because
he's really charming and he's
funny and he also has
connections with Coach, with
J.T. on the other side.
He's tight with Rob, he's
tight with Sandra.
Tyson's a huge threat.
>> PROBST: Sandra, what's the
big concern about Parvati?
>> Well, we keep going back to
the fact that she has
connections on the other side.
>> PROBST: Courtney, what's the
take on Rob?
>> There seems to be a
polarizing affect.
People either like him, or
they're really bugged by him.
You know, he's at the center
of controversy a lot of times.
>> PROBST: All right, well,
there's at least a couple of
people clearly on the hot seat,
and what appears to be a fair
amount of uncertainty about
which way this vote was going to
go.
Let's get to it.
Rob has the immunity necklace
around his neck.
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: Cannot vote for Rob.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Danielle, you're up.
>> Welcome to the big leagues.
>> You're so damn charming, and
that's what makes you dangerous.
That and your friends on the
other side.
Night-night.
>> You need to get in the ocean
and wash your ass.
I can't stand you, and I can't
wait for you to go home.
Adios.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody does have the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
>> PROBST: If anybody does have
the hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
>> I think I'm gonna take the
target off of my back.
You know, Coach, you always say
loyal, honesty and trust is
the best thing.
No matter how this comes out
tonight, I'm gonna stick to
that.
Parvati.
>> Are you serious?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Thank you.
I guess I'm playing it.
Such a gentleman.
>> PROBST: The rules of Survivor
state that if a hidden immunity
idol is played, then any votes
cast against that person will
not count, and the person with
the next highest number of votes
will be voted out.
This is, indeed, a hidden
immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Parvati will
not count.
This is a bold move by Russell.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Russell.
Two votes Russell.
Parvati.
Does not count.
We're still at two votes
Russell.
Parvati.
Does not count.
Tyson.
That's two votes-- Russell, one
vote-- Tyson.
Tyson.
We're tied.
Two votes-- Russell, two votes--
Tyson.
One vote left.
Sixth person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs.
Villains...
Tyson.
>> Oh, my God.
>> PROBST: Tyson, the tribe has
spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, that was definitely a
crazy Tribal Council.
In a moment, we're going to
bring in the Heroes for their
Tribal Council, which you will
get to listen in on while
enjoying hot dogs and soft
drinks.
I'll give you a moment to move
your torches, we'll get started.
>> Oh, man, I have nobody to
blame but myself.
I was the victim of my own
stupidity.
Russell probably gained a little
bit of respect and a little bit
of power by his risky move
today.
Giving the idol to Parvati was
kind of a shocker.
It ended up being my demise.
I wish I would have stuck to the
split vote.
I would have come out
victorious, and Russell would
have gone home.
What you gonna do?
I'm still pretty awesome.
>> PROBST: Heroes getting your
first look at the new Villain
tribe.
Tyson voted out of tonight's
Tribal Council.
All right, Heroes, as you know,
part of the reward of today's
challenge-- the Villains earned
the right to sit in and listen
in on your Tribal Council and
enjoy hot dogs and soft drinks.
(thunder rumbling)
You guys can remove the covers
and get started.
>> Damn.
(rain falling)
>> Don't drop the buns.
>> This is so evil.
>> Wasn't our idea.
>> Buns.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Rupert, you haven't
taken your eyes off that food,
even while I'm asking you the
question.
>> No. I would have already had
a couple of them dogs down.
(rolling thunder)
(loud, rumbling thunder)
>> Yes, at least it's raining on
y'all parade.
>> PROBST: Rupert, sitting this
close to the entire tribe of
Villains, it's kind of a
reflection of where we're at in
this game.
This tribe is dwindling.
They're still full, so to speak.
>> Literally and physically,
they are.
You know, the line between Hero
and Villain is so blurred right
now.
The Villains are showing the
Heroes how the hell this game is
supposed to be played.
>> PROBST: James, let's talk
about today's challenge.
There's a big sort of question
surrounding you.
Was there any talk about, "You
did great, man.
I'm so glad we kept you," or was
there even a question?
>> There were questions.
And then, I had to race J.T.,
and I lost, so I gave up...
>> PROBST: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You raced J.T.?
>> I really want the best for
the tribe, and I don't want to
obligate anybody to keep me over
here, so, I'm like this.
"Let's go get it, let's have a
race."
Well, I sucked, and the dude
from Alabama beat me.
>> PROBST: Amanda, to be fair, I
would think a lot of people
would lose, in a foot race, to
J.T.
>> It's something to consider,
because if we have a challenge
tomorrow, that's running.
I mean, it's on everyone's mind.
>> PROBST: Colby, the last few
Tribal Councils, you've been on
the outside of the
conversations, you've been in
disagreement with the vote, and
you've said, "Sooner or later,
it will be me."
What do you do in a game like
this?
Can you scramble?
>> I just went back to camp and
sat down and had a conversation
with James about how bad we both
want to be in this game, 'cause
we're the two guys in question.
>> PROBST: Did you get the
feeling from James that he
definitely wanted to still be in
this game?
>> Absolutely, and he asked me
the same thing.
>> PROBST: So, James, you
weren't sure.
>> This is pretty much one of
the baddest survivors ever
growing up.
>> I'm not that old!
>> But you know what I mean!
(laughter)
Watching the show forever.
I get here, he got slammed by
the dragon slayer.
Picked up and brought in the
van.
Today, he got beat by a cripple
and fat dude on an obstacle
course.
It's like finding out Superman
was in a big girdle.
You see the muscles, and you get
up close, and it's nothing but a
fat suit.
So, I'm, like, "Honestly, do you
want to be here?
'Cause if not, I'll stay here,
'cause I like it here."
Some of us are doers, and some
of us are sayers.
I'm more of a doer.
Like, they told me today,
there's such a thing as a banana
etiquette.
>> PROBST: Banana etiquette?
>> If you go get a banana, you
have to ask every person who's
in your vicinity if they would
like a banana.
(laughter)
Which is great, but in my world,
if your ass is hungry, you go
get a banana.
(laughter)
>> PROBST: Colby, what's it like
to hear James say, it's like
seeing Superman is wearing a fat
suit?
>> I mean, hearing that's
certainly not as bad as living
it.
You know, that's the worst.
I mean, it's a reality.
It's a reality.
Up to this point, I have not
performed as well as I would
have hoped to.
>> PROBST: All right, it is time
to get to the vote, which means,
Villains, finish what's in your
mouth...
>> Ha-ha!
>> PROBST: Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
>> Oh, my God, there's bread up
there.
>> PROBST: All right, Candice,
you have the individual immunity
necklace.
>> Keeping it.
>> PROBST: Cannot vote for
Candice.
Everybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Rupert, you're up.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Colby.
James.
One vote-- Colby, one vote--
Two votes-- James, one vote--
Colby.
James.
That's three votes-- James, one
vote-- Colby.
Seventh person voted out of
Heroes vs. Villains-- James.
That's four.
That's enough.
You need to bring your torch.
>> Bye, babe.
>> PROBST: James, the tribe has
spoken.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Have a shot for us.
>> Oh, I'm going to be good and
drunk in the next five minutes.
>> PROBST: Well, from the sounds
of tonight's Tribal Council, an
alliance was broken, and
hopefully, a tribe was unified.
Grab your torches, head back to
camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor.
Without his idol, nothing can
save Russell from the wrath of
Rob.
>> He's dangerous.
Anybody that gives away immunity
and leaves himself blank-- it's
like a suicide bomber.
You can't stop someone like
that.
If they don't care about their
own fate in the game, that's a
wild card.
He'll do anything.
>> I have banana etiquette.
That's just a little bit too
much.
But hopefully, they can finally
pacify Colby into actually being
a teammate, and actually having
the team together.
Hopefully, they'll do better.
But it's a game.
It was fun.
I just happened to have bad luck
on this thing with injuries.
And they got me a little bit
earlier than they should have.