>> JEFF PROBST: Previously on
Survivor:
When the two tribes first hit
the beach, they stayed true to
their nature.
The Heroes were heroic, and the
Villains were villainous.
The Heroes overcame injuries...
>> PROBST: ...to win the first
challenge.
They also tirelessly worked
together to build a great camp.
>> Watching these guys working
together-- it's good to be a
Hero.
>> Villains!
>> Get your evil on.
>> PROBST: The Villains did not
work together and complained
about everything.
>> PROBST: It was the perfect
environment for Russell to work
his black magic.
Russell made deals with anyone
who would listen and even roped
in Parvati.
>> PROBST: But by day two, the
game started to change.
At the Heroes' camp, J.T.
embraced the dark side by
making conflicting deals with
James and Tom.
>> You're my guy for the end.
>> All right, you got me.
>> PROBST: At the Villains'
camp, Boston Rob behaved
heroically.
He worked hard around camp and
even built a fire without
flint.
And after getting sick and
passing out, he got up and
led his tribe to a
come-from-behind victory at the
immunity challenge.
Villains win the second
immunity challenge in a row!
After their second defeat in a
row, the Heroes were
demoralized, and James lashed
out.
>> He was telling you what to
do, and everybody mouth want to
talk.
>> PROBST: At Tribal Council,
James continued his tirade.
>> You're trying to blame this
entire challenge on me?
>> PROBST: And J.T.'s duplicity
was revealed when he chose not
to honor his alliance with Tom
by voting out Tom's closest
ally, Stephenie.
Steph, the tribe has spoken.
18 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
(squeaking)
>> There's a lot of frustration,
James.
I get that.
You could have been gentler,
that's all.
Let's do what we can to get it
back on track, you know?
>> I can't believe...
>> I think we cleared up a lot
of things.
>> Yeah.
>> We aired things that needed
to be said. Um...
>> Let's work together, man.
>> That's all I want to do, man.
>> Right.
We got a good fire going.
>> I love that.
It's nice to come home to fire.
>> At Tribal Council tonight, I
mean, just a nasty turn with...
All right, Steph's going, and
then, James got to bring down,
you know, just nasty, brutish
bullying on her.
The vibe now is, everybody comes
home, puts on a happy face, and,
uh, tries to make it as pleasant
as possible to be together.
(indistinct chatter)
>> I respect you a lot, Tom.
Here's the thing, man.
I'm sorry for-for everything.
I-I knew...
>> Right.
>> Hey, listen, sometimes with
numbers, that's the way the
dice come up.
I'm a big boy.
I'm okay with that.
>> Hey, I'm sorry, man.
>> Nope, it's all good.
It's all good.
>> I'll do my best.
>> I feel betrayed by J.T., but
if he really does feel bad about
it, um, he might be the guy to
keep me alive a little longer
and buy me some extra time if I
need it.
>> Right.
It's hard to play nice after a
scene like that, but that's
exactly what we need to do.
Right?
>> Yeah.
>> To be fair, the game has been
ugly, so maybe we were naive to
think we were coming back, and
it was going to be Marquis of
Queensberry rules here and
everybody fighting fair, and...
>> Right.
>> So, we know the guys that are
playing the game, and, uh, be
smarter.
>> Yeah.
>> Be smarter.
>> Okay, hold it, hold it.
I'm going to try to get in here.
I don't know what...
>> Ugh!
Oh, it hurts!
>> Ow! Ow!
This sucks.
>> Oh.
>> Is he moving again?
>> Yeah.
>> Does your head stay on his
chest, or does it roll off?
(laughter)
Mine just rolls right off.
It won't stay.
Ew!
(laughter)
Stop it!
(laughter continues)
(laughter)
>> Ew!
>> I mean, at the end of the
day, I wanted to see what would
develop, and you notice
different things around camp.
I mean, the clearest sign...
For anybody that's going to play
Survivor in the future, I'm
going to give you the key to
figuring out who's on what team.
Watch how they sleep at night.
Whoever's sleeping next to who--
and I'm even guilty of it-- will
tell you who's aligned with who.
Because at night when you go to
sleep, you don't usually go to
sleep next to the guy who you
want to vote off.
>> All right.
Sorry.
>> It's okay.
>> I don't trust Russell's ass
at all.
At all.
I mean, he's running around with
puppy doggy eyes over Parvati
since the minute we landed here.
He won't do anything without
her.
He has to sleep next to her
every night.
Coach and Jerri are trying to do
the same thing.
That can be dangerous.
I know. I've been there.
And I know how powerful that
kind of an alliance is.
>> Our tribe has not been solid
since we've been together.
That's why I was kind of hoping
for a rainy day that would force
us all in the shelter, all day
today, and play games and talk
and do some bonding stuff and do
some empowerment stuff.
>> This is the coop, huh? Sweet!
>> If we don't become a good,
cohesive team, we will continue
to lose.
>> Get them inside.
(clucking)
>> They got out.
>> Hell, yeah!
Free chickies!
>> Oh, my gosh.
>> That's him right there.
>> Get him out of there.
>> Oh, they're right there,
y'all.
Let's just grab them.
>> Grab 'em, bro.
(loud clucking)
>> Okay, there's one of them.
>> Hold him.
>> I don't even see the other
one.
>> Oh, there he is.
>> There he is! There he is!
There he is!
>> Grab him!
>> Hang on. Don't...
Don't get him running.
>> He is now wanted, dead or
alive, so it's his choice.
>> He just went out that way,
that way, that way.
What?
>> There he goes.
He's under the shelter.
>> Surround the shelter and
let's do the same thing.
>> He's coming out the back.
>> That's good. Yeah.
>> Good.
>> Good, good, good, Tom, very,
very good...
(whooping)
>> Still got it!
>> Good job, Tom!
>> It was a neat experience,
wrangling the chickens as a
tribe.
Um, that's what we need.
>> So in that sense, the
chickens getting out was
supposed to happen to help us
bond.
(Rupert snorts)
>> They're not going to kill
that thing so fast.
>> I can't believe that thing is
just sitting there, dude.
>> So, what's up, man?
>> The first vote is the most
important vote.
>> Right.
>> You got to be careful.
That's what I wanted to talk to
you about.
You got to be careful, 'cause
people want to have any excuse
to not be the vote.
What is that excuse?
"Oh, Russell and Parvati are
together."
>> Right.
>> Whatever it is...
>> Everybody's going to use an
excuse so it's not them.
Russell, um, is walking on very
thin ice.
Parvati, in my opinion, is the
most dangerous player on our
tribe.
>> And it's not that we're cool
or nothing-- me and Parvati.
It's because, uh, she's a good
asset to the team.
>> For him to be following
around Parvati is no strategy
at all.
It's puppy love.
She's got the charm.
She's got the smile.
For some reason, when she pays
attention to you, you feel like
you light up.
It's not that people don't see
it.
It's just that they are allured
by her charm, and they're taken
by it.
They're smitten by it.
It's unbelievable.
>> What's the deal?
>> Uh...
>> About what?
>> Who can kind of...
>> Uh, ultimately, I'm trying
to get a feel on Russell on what
he's thinking about Parvati,
and..
>> And not for nothing, but
I've seen this go down before.
You got to be careful, you know,
the way you're hanging out with
her and everything.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> And I mean, she might... she
might not be the strongest, and
she got a lot of friends on the
other side.
>> Right.
>> And we see you marching
around with her, so...
>> Yeah.
>> ...you have to understand
our concern.
>> Oh, I understand it.
>> Am I right, or am I right?
>> Yeah, you're totally right,
and it's like it's ostracizing
you.
>> Right.
>> And you got to be cool on
that, man.
>> Man.
>> I mean, what else can you do?
>> You've got to do it.
I have no choice.
That would be my... the end of
my game...
Everybody knows Coach is a big
joke, so he can go around
flapping his jaws all he wants.
The thing with Rob-- he thinks
he's the boss of the camp, like
that's my daddy.
Well, I'm the daddy around here.
But I got to listen to this fool
like he's in control.
But that's what I have to do to
get to the top.
That's what I'm going to have
to do until he's gone.
He don't know who he's messing
with.
Nobody knows who they're
messing with around here.
It's Russell Hantz.
Give me a break!
>> And he's, like, "No, no.
She'll know something's coming.
man.
Just keep doing what you're
doing, brother."
"Keep doing what you're
doing."
>> Wow.
>> He is after you.
>> He is demented.
>> I didn't want your name to
even be on the block.
It worries me because of that,
so I was... I was even trying to
convince him...
>> I'm used to it, honestly.
>> I was even trying to convince
him another way.
>> I've dodged a few bullets.
Why do they always want to vote
me out?
I don't know.
I'm just a sweet, innocent,
little girl, really.
(laughs)
>> And then Rob came over there
and said, "Give us your word
you'll get rid of her."
I said, "Dude, do you seriously
think I'm here to hook up with
a girl?
I mean, please."
>> I made an alliance really
early on with Russell, and so, I
don't know what I'm going to
have to do, but who else am I
going to be with right now
besides Russell?
I don't trust anyone, and I
actually do trust him, even
though he's kind of a lunatic.
>> I said I'll show you how to
get rid of her, and we'll get
rid of her-- and then y'all can
trust me then, so she's gone.
Okay?
And that's it.
(Parvati laughs)
>> If I'm gone, you're gone
next.
>> Yeah.
>> You know that.
>> Yeah. Bye.
>> So I'm three days out,
basically, from the, you know,
95 degrees, hot as hell, started
throwing up.
My gums were, like, bleeding a
little bit.
I mean, I started getting these
big sores on my face.
I'm, like, all right, what's
this?
>> Is this the same story as
last night?
>> Not the same story, my
friend.
>> It's not? It's awful similar.
>> No, it's not, trust me.
>> Okay.
>> So it took me eight days to
get from, uh... de Los
Angeles...
Yeah, I had my compass set on,
uh, east-due-east, and I was
hoping I would make it. So...
>> (chuckles): Rob thinks he's
running the show, and Coach
thinks he's running the show.
But I'm gonna take control of
that.
They want to play rough?
I can play rough.
King Rustall can get rid of the
machete.
You know what happens then?
Getting rid of the machete will
cause conflict in this camp.
Rob's going to go crazy.
The tribe's going to go crazy.
Everything's going to go
haywire.
Can't find the machete, can't
eat the chickens, can't open
the coconuts, can't start fire.
And that's a good thing.
>> 95 degrees, hot as hell, and
I was thinking to myself, what
am I going to do?
I've got no water.
>> This is going to be
wonderful, 'cause it's not just
going to be the machete.
Old Boston Rob likes that hat,
don't he?
I think he will go nuts without
his little "B" hat.
I don't even like the Boston
Red Sox.
It's the Houston Astros, baby.
>> COACH: ♪ Oh... ♪
>> ♪ I...
Give you...
All of my strength. ♪
>> Who wants clam?
Russell, Rob, Parvati?
Nobody?
>> I'm fine without a clam
right now.
>> Courtney?
'Cause I don't want it to spoil
'cause it's out of the water
and I don't want it to... you
know, go to waste, and I don't
want to eat it all, either.
>> Well, just eat a little bit
of it and throw it away.
>> All right.
>> Machete?
>> Damn.
I did find one giant clam that
was good for five or six bites
of food, but nobody cared.
You know, I'm used to seeing on
Survivor where somebody brings
a fish in this size, and the
entire tribe swarms him hoping
to get an ounce of meat, and you
eat what you can eat when you
can get it and you don't ask
questions, 'cause you don't
know where your next food is
coming from.
>> Randy, this thing cuts good.
>> Ew.
>> Got to eat.
You don't like it?
>> You want a white piece?
Of this?
(Parvati spits)
>> Sorry.
>> No?
>> I can't eat it.
It makes me gag.
>> No, we're not gonna waste
this on you.
>> Mm-mm, don't do it.
>> We won't.
(laughter)
>> Survivor, in so many ways,
is like the real world--
you don't get ahead by being
smart...
clever, hardworking.
You get ahead, unfortunately,
with a pretty smile and being
able to schmooze people.
And Parvati is the queen.
You know, this whole game is
designed to mess with
everybody's nerves, and it
works.
>> The team's only as good as
its weakest player.
And that's why we never get
anything done around camp.
Because the weakest players
just sit there and think that
they can look pretty and cute
and have everything handed to
them. Right?
>> Well... let's vote them out.
>> I personally can't stand it
when I see people that are
loafers and people that are
weak.
It's not fair.
It's just simply unjust.
And it's selfish, and it's
egotistical that "I can do
nothing, sit back, feed me
grapes like a Greek goddess."
It's just... the whole thing
just stinks.
>> You know, I think you're a
great player, and, um... I'd
like to make it to the end.
>> Yeah, I do, too.
>> But if somebody's not
talking to me strategy, they're
talking to somebody else.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And when you come talking
with somebody on the day we're
going to Tribal Council, that
doesn't count.
You know what I mean?
'Cause you need a favor then.
>> Candice is beginning to
scare me a lot.
She's much more strategical
than I gave her credit for to
begin with.
>> I think Cirie is trustworthy
if... she feels safe within...
>> If she feels safe.
Candice may be the next one
to go, in my opinion, but, you
know, it's not all up to me.
Not in this group.
>> What are your thoughts?
Everything still good?
>> It's hard to trust anyone
out here right now.
>> Mm. Tell me about it.
(laughs)
>> Okay.
>> I got her.
I can get rid of her. (laughs)
I can tell a story when I need
to.
I think my lying ability is...
probably better than it should
be.
Considering I don't do it very
much in everyday life, I'm
pretty good at it out here.
(water splashing)
>> I'm-I'm nervous now.
>> About what?
>> About us.
>> You're nervous about me and
you?
>> Yeah.
>> Why? What...
>> I hear-hear stuff.
>> Tell me what you hear.
>> That you don't trust me,
and...
>> Who said that?
(Cirie laughs)
>> I don't want to say who said
it-- I just want to...
>> Well, it doesn't matter who
said it, 'cause it's not true.
I'm thinking, where did that
come from, because I have never
said that.
Either somebody is trying to
make sure that she and I don't
trust each other, or I'm
thinking there's something
weird going on.
Did you tell Cirie in any way
that... I said or that I don't
trust her?
>> Absolutely not.
>> Okay.
She's hearing around that I
said I don't trust her.
>> I've never heard you talk
bad about Cirie.
>> No, and I haven't.
Cirie just told me that
somebody is telling her that I
said I don't trust her.
>> I don't have any idea what
you're talking about.
I just wish you would just chill
out just for a second, just for
a little while, and then we'd be
all right.
Candice, I mean, she's a nut.
Everybody's going to play with
Candice 'cause she's hustling
a little bit too much.
I don't know what's wrong with
the girl.
Like, I don't even care about
the whole... we can't even focus
on all that stuff right now.
It's pointless to even worry
about all that.
I just want to get to
challenges and win.
♪ ♪
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
Villains getting your first
look at the new Hero tribe.
Stephenie voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
>> Oh...
>> PROBST: You guys ready to
get to your next challenge?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you are
going to square off, one on one,
sumo style.
Using a large, heavy bag, you
will attempt to knock your
opponent into the mud.
Two rules-- you must keep both
hands on the bag at all times;
cannot use your legs as a
weapon.
First tribe to score eight wins
immunity, safe from the vote.
Losers go to Tribal Council,
where somebody will be voted
out of this game.
In addition, you are once again
playing for reward, and it is a
doozy.
First, we have luxury items.
Each of you brought one item
from home to remind you of the
love you left behind.
In addition, you are playing
for coffee, sugar...
>> Coffee!
>> PROBST: ...and a week's worth
of rice.
Worth playing for?
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: Villains, you are
sitting out two people.
You must sit out two women.
>> Me and Courtney.
>> PROBST: Courtney and Sandra
sitting out.
You two take a spot on the
bench.
Everybody else, I'll give you a
minute to strategize and change
clothes if you like.
All right, Tom heading out for
the Heroes, going up against
Russell.
Tom for the Heroes taking on
Russell for the Villains in our
first round.
>> Do it, Tom.
>> Show him!
>> PROBST: Tom did this
challenge in his season in
Palau, and he was victorious.
Let's see how it goes against
Russell.
Survivors ready?
>> Let's go, Russell!
>> PROBST: Go!
Tom not messing around!
Sends Russell into the mud
easily.
(others shouting, cheering)
Heroes lead one-zip.
>> It's all right, Russell!
Come on!
>> PROBST: Next round, it is
Parvati for the Villains,
Candice for the Heroes.
>> You be strong!
>> PROBST: Heroes lead one-zip.
Playing to eight.
Survivors ready?
>> Attack her, Candice!
Attack her!
>> PROBST: Go!
Parvati now has Candice near
the edge.
Parvati's now down.
Candice has Parvati on her back.
>> Come on, Parvati!
Keep fighting!
>> PROBST: Candice using her
body.
Parvati back on her feet.
Candice has Parvati on the run
again!
Candice now takes Parvati out!
Parvati first in the mud!
Heroes score!
Heroes lead two-zip.
>> Good job, Parvati.
>> PROBST: Next two.
It is Rupert, aggressive and
ready, taking on the dragon
slayer... Coach.
>> Come on, Rupe!
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
(shouting)
Rain coming down now for this
battle.
Coach going to the face of
Rupert.
(overlapping shouting)
>> Come on, Rupert!
>> PROBST: Rupert has Coach.
Coach, get your hand on the bag!
No, no.
Replaying.
(Coach yelling)
No! No! No!
(Coach yells)
Coach! Coach?
>> You lost. Come over here.
>> PROBST: No!
>> What?
>> You lost.
>> PROBST: Do over.
Coach, inadvertent or not, you
used your arm.
(thunder rumbling)
>> Oh!
Take that anger and point it to
the pirate, not me.
>> Let's go!
Never mind that. Let's go.
Finish the job, Coach.
>> Look, you got to get lower
and get meaner!
>> You got to attack!
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Survivors ready?
>> Come on, Coach!
>> PROBST: Go!
(overlapping shouting)
Villains want to score.
Coach going for the head.
Coach in trouble.
Coach in the mud for the
Villains.
Heroes score!
>> Yeah.
>> PROBST: Heroes lead
three-zip.
Next round.
Jerri Manthey for the Villains
taking on Cirie for the Heroes.
>> Cirie!
>> Whup her ass!
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on!
>> PROBST: Cirie goes after
Jerri.
She has her on the run.
Jerri down.
Jerri in the mud.
Heroes score again.
Heroes lead four-zip.
All right, next two.
Heroes-- J.T. taking on Tyson.
>> Here we go, Tyson.
>> Go, Tyson!
>> That's the way you do it.
>> Bet off!
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Tyson clearing his
mud off in front of J.T.'s
area.
Heroes lead four-zip.
Survivors ready?
Go!
J.T. comes out hard and strong.
Tyson not backing down.
>> Get him, Tyson!
>> Tys, get down!
(overlapping shouting)
>> PROBST: J.T. going after
Tyson.
Tyson in trouble.
Tyson in the mud for the
Villains!
Heroes score.
Heroes lead five-zip.
>> That's who we are.
>> PROBST: Next round, Danielle
for the Villains taking on
Amanda for the Heroes.
>> Come on, Amanda!
>> PROBST: Survivors ready?
Go!
(overlapping shouting)
Danielle going hard against
Amanda.
Amanda spins around, stays
alive.
Danielle pushing hard.
Amanda fighting back.
Now Amanda has Danielle on the
run.
Heroes score again!
Heroes lead six-zip, making it
look easy.
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Next two.
It is Colby...
>> Come on, Colby.
>> PROBST: ...for the Heroes
taking on Boston Rob for the
Villains.
>> Rob!
>> PROBST: Heroes lead six-zip.
We're playing to eight.
Survivors ready?
Go!
>> Come on, Rob!
>> PROBST: Colby goes strong.
Rob slips, but stays on.
Rob squirming to stay alive.
>> Get him, Robbie.
>> PROBST: Rob has Colby.
Colby fighting to get back up.
(overlapping chatter)
Heads are butting.
>> Get him, Colby!
>> PROBST: Colby has Rob down
now.
Rob trying to stay low and keep
his leverage.
Colby pushes Rob into the mud.
Heroes score again.
Heroes seven, Villains nothing.
>> Good luck, man.
That's a strong opponent you're
going to have.
>> PROBST: All right, next two.
James for the Heroes, taking on
Randy for the Villains.
Heroes need one point to win
immunity and a big reward.
>> All right, Randy, do your
best, Randy!
>> Come on. Get down in there.
>> Let's get it, baby.
>> You like beating up old men?
>> Come on, big man.
>> Grab the bag, baby.
Don't talk now.
>> PROBST: Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
James goes after Randy, and with
one push, Randy in the mud!
Heroes win immunity and reward.
(cheering)
>> Yeah!
(whooping)
>> Yeah, that was real
heroesque.
>> Real classy.
>> Get your ... out of there.
>> I told you, you were on the
wrong team, James.
>> PROBST: Heroes,
congratulations.
For the first time, immunity
is yours.
>> Yeah!
>> Yes!
>> PROBST: In addition to
immunity, you have coffee,
sugar, rice for a week and
some luxury items.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Enjoy the night off from Tribal.
Cirie's got the cleanest hands.
>> Yes, you take that.
>> PROBST: Villains, Tribal
Council for you guys.
One of the ten of you will be
the third person voted out of
this game.
Should be an interesting
afternoon.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
(laughter)
>> Oh, dude.
Feel your hair.
>> Dude, come on!
>> Oh, my God, it's a lot of
mud.
>> Yeah, those Heroes were
waiting to wallop on us a bit.
I guess they must have all
eaten steroid sandwiches right
before the, uh... the challenge.
They were all crazy-eyed, and,
uh, it was almost scary to look
in their faces.
Not that it was intimidating,
but I worried for their sanity.
>> There you go.
>> A mess.
Everyone's a mess.
>> Little pigpen.
From the, uh... the Muppets?
>> The Peanuts.
>> Peanuts.
>> You don't even have to be
told that your name is on the
block.
You can just sense it.
I'm the oldest guy in the game,
I'm the oldest guy in this
tribe, and Russell and Boston
Rob and probably Tyson are
falling for the oldest trick in
the book since cave man days
that these girls can get what
they want if they bat their
eyes and flirt.
>> Scrubbing is involved.
>> Yeah.
>> Parvati is a threat right
now, even though she may be in
a minority in this tribe.
But if we overlook her because
she's got a pretty smile and a
nice wiggle, she's going to be
trouble when she meets up with
her old friends James, Cirie
and Amanda.
And we could all pay dearly for
not taking care of business
right now, and by taking care
of business, I mean getting her
out of here as soon as possible.
>> No, I'm...
I have not made my bet yet.
>> Answer the question.
>> I have not made my bet yet.
>> I hardly ever even talk
strategy.
The only person I talk strategy
with is Randy, because he's a
a super fan.
>> Oh, Coach, please.
Every time I see you, you're
running around grabbing someone,
trying to talk to them.
>> That is not true.
That is totally not true.
That is not true.
I don't lie.
You know, Parvati came at me
real aggressive in the water
today saying, "You know, are you
targeting me?"
I kept trying to fend off her
question, and yet she thinks
that she can bat her eyelashes
and wiggle her hips and roll
down a very short bathing suit
already to make it even more
skimpy, and everybody will
follow her around.
Well, maybe Russell will, maybe
other people will.
Maybe Tyson will.
I sure as hell won't.
>> I don't want to go, and I
don't think I'm the weakest.
I think I would be a poor choice
to go.
I think you could use me to your
advantage.
>> That stuff doesn't work on
me.
I've been coaching college
soccer for women for 13 years,
and I've never had one of those
girls bat their eyes at me and
make a difference in their
playing time.
>> Never.
Fear's never controlled me,
and flirting has never
controlled me.
I'm my own man.
>> Really?
>> I'm going to make my
decision...
>> I just want you to know.
I don't think any flirting
controls anyone.
>> But I do like flirting with
you.
>> I think it's ridiculous that
people think that.
>> So out here with a million
dollars on the line, certainly
isn't going to happen.
And anybody that lets it happen
will be a fool.
>> Parvati has too many friends
on the other side, and they're
controlling that game over
there.
Randy has no friends anywhere,
here or there.
She's dangerous.
Randy is not dangerous.
What do you think?
>> Amanda, come here.
Are you hearing this?
>> I heard him.
It has to be a group effort.
It can't be two or three
going...
You know what I'm saying?
>> I know.
>> Like, it has to be the
majority, and what is the
majority?
Randy is weak.
Why would we want to weaken our
tribe?
>> I just know she has a ton of
friends over there.
>> I'd rather take Randy out
than Parvati.
>> So, let's make a decision.
People are coming.
>> Parvati is like a virus.
That girl needs to go.
She has a way of just, like,
roping people in, even when they
don't want anything to do with
her.
I'm going to find out how to
bottle that up and use it in my
real life, 'cause it's pretty
powerful stuff.
>> I'm safe tonight.
You're safe tonight.
We know the two people whose
names are there, um, and I don't
know what to do.
You know?
I don't know where you're at.
>> I'm going to tell you like
this.
I'm not in trouble.
>> I don't want to, either.
>> Therefore, I don't need...
>> I feel the same way.
>> All I'm going to do is,
where's everybody at?
Boom, that's it, done.
That's it.
If they all want him out, that's
who I'll write.
If they all want her out, that's
That's it.
Let me go do this thing.
>> Okay.
>> It doesn't matter, either.
It's just a matter...
He's, obviously, the weakest
link, so...
>> Yeah. I mean, this is a lot
of...
>> We don't have to play that
card, but a lot of people want
to, and that's... it's
overall just...
>> I know, but I'm just going
to say it again because...
Everyone...
I think everyone has their own
strength...
>> Yeah, but if we vote him out
tonight, they'll have to sit out
one of their strong guys in the
next challenge, so that will
give us a fighting chance.
>> I mean, we don't know.
>> Yeah, you don't know.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm just saying that
that's...
>> Well, if you're going to say
not Randy, then you have to say
someone else?
>> I don't have to say.
>> Why not?
>> Because I don't know.
I'm just trying to figure out
what's going on.
>> Well, but if you're trying to
get someone to vote for someone,
you have to say who.
>> I'm not trying to get anybody
to vote for anybody yet.
I don't know what's going on,
honestly.
Moments like that drive me up
the wall.
That girl-- she thinks that she
can make people do whatever she
wants, and people are, but I'm
not.
I am not.
I'm at the point right now,
where every time I'm around
here, I just want to punch her
in the face.
That's all I can think about is
just taking her down.
Boy, I'll tell you what.
>> Jerri's annoying.
(laughs)
I mean, she is the fakest
Fakey McGee I've ever met.
I know she's running around
behind my back talking about me.
She's just, like, a bitter old
cougar, and I think her days are
numbered, too.
>> I loved it when I saw
Stephenie gone, 'cause that
should make it clear to you
what's going on.
It should make it clear to Rob
If you guys don't see that,
you're next.
I don't have a clue what you
were talking to Parvati about,
and I don't even want to know.
But... this is Micronesia 2.0.
>> Oh, it is.
>> And if you guys don't see
that, I don't want to play the
game with you anymore, I really
don't.
I'm not going to scramble today
like a dead man walking,
because...
>> No, I'm gonna be scrambling.
>> Because if I am dead man
walking... (laughs)
a lot of my friends are next.
And, you know, I'll see you in
Loser's Lodge.
I'll buy you a beer.
>> There's nobody out here
that's honorable.
There's nobody out here that's
honorable... anymore.
Except for me.
I hate to pontificate about
that but, you know, Martin
Luther King says that the
greatest measure of a man is
not in the way he handles times
of comfort, but in the way he
rises with controversy and
challenge.
There's always hope.
The last thing we have in life
or in this game is hope that
the impossible happens, that we
dare to dream, that Randy's
going to wake up in this camp
tomorrow.
So yes, there's still hope.
While I still have a breath and
a brain cell in my brain, I
will fight for him.
>> PROBST: Behind each of you
is a torch.
Go ahead and grab one.
Dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual of
Tribal Council, because in this
game fire represents your life.
As long as you have fire,
you're still in the game.
When your fire is gone, so are
you.
Sandra, when you play a game
like this with 20 people who
have all played-- some two,
some three times-- how big a
consideration is past
relationships, whether within
this tribe or people that are
on the other tribe?
>> There's a lot of things we
take into consideration.
One, who's won before.
Who's been out here three times.
Who has friends on another
tribe.
For instance, with Parvati,
we're thinking, okay, Cirie's
over there, James is over
there, Amanda's over there.
Like, how far do we want them
to go, and then, once we merge,
are we screwed?
>> PROBST: Parvati, you're
shaking your head.
>> Yeah, everyone's nervous
about me flipping if a merge
comes.
All I can say is that I want to
stick true to this tribe.
But, you know, it's words, and
in this game, your word doesn't
mean that much.
It's really your actions that
matter.
>> PROBST: Russell, what kind
of weight do you give that?
>> I think it is a huge
advantage that somebody might
know three or four people on
the other tribe.
It's a huge advantage.
>> PROBST: Jerri, do you think
tonight's vote should be based
on performances at challenges?
>> I think the physical side of
this is very important for us.
This is our first loss, and we
don't want to lose any more.
But I know myself I'm still
taking into account all the
other factors, relationships
and all that sort of thing.
>> PROBST: So for you, past
relationships, whether within
your own tribe or the other
tribe, is a big factor?
>> I think it should be a big
factor for everyone.
>> PROBST: Sandra, is there a
leader on this tribe?
>> Well, it all depends on what
we're doing.
If we're building the shelter,
we start listening to him, and
then when it gets too much,
then we go off on our own.
And then Coach'll delegate,
"You do this and I'll do this
and we'll go do that," but then
when you look, Coach is gone
two miles out.
>> Sandra, you only mentioned
me in that, and I don't know if
it's a jibe at me, but that's a
bunch of bull.
I collected firewood for three
hours, thank you very much.
Nobody's out there collecting
firewood like I am.
I've been working hard around
camp, and I resent you for
saying that.
In fact, why do you think we
have the worst shelter in
Survivor history?
Because it's like herding cats.
>> It's not the worst shelter
in Survivor history-- I was in
that one, actually.
>> I'd argue that I was
also a part of one of those
contenders.
>> I want to say one other
thing to Sandra.
If you think I'm not pulling my
weight around camp and in the
challenges, then put my name
down on the paper tonight.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I'm saying.
>> Well, that's what you made it
sound like.
You made it sound like I'm an
ass that sits there that wants
to be a leader and then doesn't
do any work.
>> And we ain't got a machete!
We haven't had a machete all
day.
>> PROBST: What do you mean, you
have no machete?
>> It grew legs and walked off.
(Probst laughs)
>> We have three chickens,
though.
>> PROBST: Parvati, you guys
are literally laughing about
how bad it is at camp.
>> We're kind of a tribe full
of misfits, Jeff.
We're the Villains.
>> Russell, what are you making
of this tribe you're on?
>> It's definitely different.
The dodos I played with last
time couldn't hold a candle to
any one of these players.
>> Mm...
>> So it's fun, but it's a lot
harder, because you have
everybody playing the game.
But that's what I like, and
that's what I want to see, and
that's what I respect.
>> PROBST: Rob, given how well
you guys have done overall at
the challenges so far, I'm a
little surprised at the lack of
cohesiveness within the group.
Do you think just coming to
Tribal Council alone will
impact that when you guys go
back to camp?
>> No. I don't think so.
I think that when we have a
challenge, we know what we have
to do, and we figure out a way
very quickly on how to
accomplish it.
At camp, it's a different story.
There's nobody to tell us, "You
need to make your shelter
better," or "You need to
collect firewood."
There's not that sense of
urgency.
So I don't think it will change.
>> PROBST: All right, it is
time to vote.
Russell, you're up.
>> It was either you or me
tonight, and I wasn't gonna go
down without a fight.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
Once the votes are read, the
decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Randy.
Rob.
One vote Rob.
Randy.
Two votes Randy, one vote Rob.
That's three votes Randy, one
vote Rob.
Randy.
Four votes Randy, one vote Rob.
That's five votes Randy, one
vote Rob.
Third person voted out of
Survivor: Heroes vs.
Villains...
Randy.
That's six; that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Randy, the tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
Well, even though we're only
eight days into the game, if
you don't get your camp life
together, it will catch up to
you, and you will be coming
back to Tribal, and more people
will be going home.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor:
Coach melts down.
>> Why does nobody say anything
good about me?
>> I think I'll go this way.
>> PROBST: The Hero tribe
splinters apart while looking
for the hidden immunity idol.
>> This is not a group effort.
It's every man for himself.
>> PROBST: And the clock is
ticking on Russell.
>> Russell's a bonehead.
It's time for him to go home.
>> It was definitely a mistake
for this tribe not to vote out
Parvati, but I knew Parvati
wasn't gonna go home, so I
decided to shoot a bullet Bob's
way, send a little message.
Whether anybody gets that
message, I don't know.
I hope it comes back and haunts
each and every one of them.
I never felt a part of this
tribe, so, you know, good luck
to them.