>> JEFF PROBST: Previously, on
Survivor:
The Heroes and Villains merged
with even numbers.
>> Good to see you, brother.
>> PROBST: The Heroes thought
they had the upper hand when
Russell promised his allegiance.
>> This is where I stand.
I swear on my kids that I am on
board with y'all.
>> PROBST: But he was only
reeling them in.
>> Hook, line and sinker.
>> PROBST: Sandra warned the
Heroes not to trust Russell...
but only Rupert believed her.
>> If Russell is playing us...
>> He's not.
Do not believe Sandra.
>> He's on the Villain side for
a reason.
>> PROBST: At the last
challenge, Danielle got the
immunity necklace around her
neck and the Heroes tried to
put a noose around Parvati's.
>> They're trying to vote me
out.
>> Yeah, they want you gone.
>> PROBST: Russell gave up his
hidden immunity idol to save
his queen, but Parvati was only
using him as a pawn.
Unbeknownst to him, she had a
second secret idol of her own.
>> Two little green men
protecting me.
>> PROBST: At a game-changing
Tribal Council, the Heroes
switched their vote to Jerri.
Parvati, sensing something was
wrong, made a huge move.
>> Sandra, that's for you.
Jerri, that one's for you, too.
>> PROBST: She played both her
idols to save the Villains and
send home J.T...
leaving Russell wondering who's
really in charge.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
>> Well, it was a good one, you
guys.
(laughter)
It really was, actually.
>> Yeah, it was.
It really was.
I didn't see that coming at all.
>> And now they got secrets
going around?
What the hell is up with that?
So, Parv, where did you find
the second idol?
>> At the Outback Challenge.
(Jerri gasps, Parvati laughs)
>> And you didn't tell me
anything about it, when I saved
your ass, and I've been doing...
>> I wanted it to be a surprise.
>> It's not a surprise.
You lied to me.
That's how I feel.
>> How did I lie to you?
>> 'Cause you didn't tell me
about it.
Danielle knew about it.
>> Your ass was never in danger.
>> We found it together.
We were gonna surprise you...
>> Yeah, well, you surely took
the one I gave you, to save you
again.
>> I know.
I was going to save Jerri.
>> It pisses me off that y'all
didn't tell me.
>> Oh, chill out.
>> Hell, no!
>> I didn't tell anyone.
>> Whatever, whatever.
Keep on... y-you can talk all
you want, but it is what it is
for me.
>> Okay, well, you can be mad
if you want, but I don't see
any harm done in keeping it a
secret.
Russell likes to be in control,
'cause he thinks he's the
godfather of this game.
And I think having me have an
idol that he didn't know about
made him feel like he wasn't in
control, and... scared a little
bit.
But that's kind of what I
wanted, anyways.
(laughs)
>> You were right-- he should've
listened to...
>> I tried.
>> Listen, um, the four of us
are good, but we're going to
see what's going on there to
break them up.
>> All right.
>> There's no way you're going
to break up Danielle, Parvati
and Russell.
When they first came over, I
had a chance with Sandra.
I tried, I went to the Heroes
and tried to tell them not to
trust Russell.
My Heroes did not want to
believe me.
With all that has happened, I
don't know how easy it will be
to pull Sandra back in.
She opened the door once.
My only hope is to maybe get
Sandra to open the door again.
(whales singing)
>> Crazy night.
You guys pulled a good one.
>> Yup.
It was just a regular vote,
regular night.
>> Wow.
That was a good one.
I'm impressed.
>> But, uh, when it comes down
to the top six, things have to
happen.
And right now the ship is
sinking.
You know that.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> And somebody, one person,
has to jump, and that one
person is going to be very
crucial to what happens later
on in the game.
We don't trust Sandra right now.
That's why I need to pull
somebody else in.
And I think I can trust Candice,
because Candice knows that her
butt's in a sling right now
and she has no other way to go.
If you're the last one standing,
you won't be the last one, you
won't go with number six, I can
guarantee that.
>> Yup, yup.
>> I don't want to sit here and
say you're going to go to the
top three, but it's a strong
possibility.
>> Well, just let me know.
>> Okay, I'll talk to you later.
>> All right.
>> I think that the right way
to go is Candice.
One hundred percent, she's ready
to freaking burn her house down.
It's huge in the game that we
have numbers.
Now it doesn't even matter
what Sandra wants to do because
Candice is going to flip.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to
today's reward challenge?
>> Yes.
>> PROBST: For today's
challenge, you will compete in a
Survivor version of
shuffleboard.
You'll be randomly divided into
teams of three-- black team,
blue team and red team.
One at a time, you'll slide
your puck across the board.
The team whose puck ends up
closest to the center of the
"X" wins reward.
Want to know what you're
playing for?
>> OTHERS: Yes. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
>> PROBST: Robert Louis
Stevenson is most famous for
writing the novel Treasure
Island.
He spent his last years and is
buried here in Samoa.
The winning team will go to his
home, which is now a museum,
where you will enjoy a
screening of the movie
Treasure Island.
>> OTHERS: Aw... Nice! Cool!
>> PROBST: You'll spend the
night, get a good night's sleep
in a real bed, return to camp
in the morning.
>> And there'll probably be a
clue to the hidden immunity
idol at today's reward, so I'm
hoping and praying that myself,
Danielle, Russell or Jerri
goes on that reward and finds
that clue-- just to keep the
power in our hands.
>> PROBST: Worth playing for?
>> OTHERS: Yes. Yes.
>> PROBST: We'll draw for teams,
we'll get started.
All right, we have our three
teams.
Candice, Parvati and Jerri--
the black team.
Rupert, Russell, Sandra-- the
red team.
Colby, Amanda, Danielle-- the
blue team.
Black, you're up first. Candice.
>> Get it, girl.
>> PROBST: Candice with the
first shot.
>> Eagle eyes.
>> PROBST: Everybody gets two
shots.
You'll go one at a time.
Right down the middle.
Good spot-- could get knocked
around a little bit.
Sandra with the first shot for
the red team.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: Sandra off the board.
Danielle first up for the blue
team.
Danielle comes up short.
Parvati up for the black team.
Red team, you're up.
>> Ooh!
>> PROBST: Nice shot for the red
team.
That is the mark to beat.
Amanda up for the blue team.
Amanda comes up short.
>> Come on, Jerri!
>> PROBST: Good toss by Jerri.
Red still the mark to beat.
Rupert gives a toss.
And look at that!
>> OTHERS: Oh! Whoa!
>> PROBST: The red team very
close now.
Colby up for the blue team.
Not quite close enough.
Everybody's had one toss.
Round two. Candice.
>> Oh!
>> Candice was trying to knock
those reds right off the board.
Good idea. Didn't work.
Sandra up for the red team.
That was just a wasted shot
there.
Blue, you're up.
And a nice toss!
(shouts, clapping)
Danielle knocks one red peg out
of the way.
The other red peg is still the
closest by about a half an inch.
Parvati, your last shot.
Nothing changes after that shot.
Russell up for the red team.
Oh... Russell.
>> Lame.
>> PROBST: On purpose?
>> Right dead in the middle for
the "X."
>> PROBST: Blue, you're up.
A lot of obstacles in the way
of getting to that "X" now.
Amanda comes up short.
This is the last shot for the
black team.
Good toss but doesn't help.
Black team is out of it now
unless something happens.
Rupert with the last toss for
the red team.
Comes up short.
One shot left in this challenge.
It belongs to Colby Donaldson.
You know what you have to do.
You either need to get rid of
this red puck or get yours in
tighter.
>> Yeah! Yeah!
>> PROBST: Colby does it for the
blue tribe!
>> Yeah!
>> PROBST: Blue wins reward!
(Colby whoops)
>> PROBST: Candice, Parvati,
Jerri, Rupert, Sandra, Russell,
you guys head out, head back to
camp.
>> Nice job, guys.
>> PROBST: Got nothing for you.
>> We're eating all the rice, so
don't come back looking for it.
>> PROBST: All right, Colby,
Danielle, Amanda, big reward.
Nice job.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Enjoy it.
>> Thank you.
Oh, my goodness.
>> This is Robert Louis
Stevenson's home.
Robert Louis Stevenson wrote 13
books while he was here in
Samoa.
>> Oh! A bed!
>> We have three books here,
first addition...
I will take you to the next
room.
>> At the reward, my main focus
was finding the clue to the
hidden immunity idol.
Can I see this for a second?
Oh, my God!
Because Parvati played two last
time, there has to be one in
play this time.
So the whole time, I was
thinking, "Oh, my God, where
could this clue be?"
Like, I am not leaving here
without it.
I have to get it.
(dramatic music playing)
Sitting on the bed, watching
Treasure Island, I didn't enjoy
any of it.
I was too busy thinking, "Where
could this clue be?
It's got to be in this room."
>> Popcorn's good, huh?
>> Yeah, it's really good.
Wow.
I found the clue in the bowl of
popcorn.
I am freaking out.
This is, like, so much power
right now.
This could be a million dollars.
But Amanda was really
suspicious.
She literally gets up out of the
bed, sits right next me.
I'm, like, is she kidding me
right now?
>> Could you guys scoot over a
little?
>> Whatcha doing, Amanda?
>> Nothing.
Wow.
Why am I getting, like...
Amanda, I'll seriously grab it
out of your hand.
>> Will you just relax for a
second?
>> Hey, give it back to me!
>> What are you doing?
You're a psychopath!
>> It's not yours.
>> Yes, it is!
Amanda...
>> I saw it there!
>> Give it to me!
You're kidding me-- I found it!
>> Oh, my God!
>> Give me back the clue.
Can you give it back to me,
please?
>> No.
>> Are you serious?
>> It's not yours-- it was in
the room.
>> I found it.
You're psychotic for, like,
doing what you just did.
You're really psychotic.
Colby, are you serious, what she
just did?
>> I didn't even see what
happened.
I was watching Treasure Island.
>> We... we have a problem,
obviously.
>> What's our... what's our
resolution?
>> Can you tell her to give it
back to me so I can have it in
my hand 'cause I found it?
And this is ridiculous.
>> I mean, this is our life in
the game; it's not ridiculous to
me.
>> It's ridiculous that you
grabbed it the way you did.
>> It was out of...
(all talking)
...it was out of desperation.
>> I'm, like, shaking right now.
>> It's your clue, Danielle,
it's your clue-- you found it.
>> Yes, but I would like it back
in my hand.
>> Give it... It's okay.
>> I need a glass of wine.
>> Yeah, so in the end, I ended
up giving the clue back and gave
it to Danielle, like an idiot.
And then Colby wasn't backing
me up, and I was just, like,
"Oh, my God."
I was just, like, "Are you
kidding me?"
Oh!
(squawking)
(indistinct talking)
>> SEVERAL: Hey!
>> Look at you guys!
>> Welcome back!
>> Hey, guys.
>> And if me and Russell and
Rupert had won that...
>> It would've been really
funny.
>> Like, the three of us barely
fit in.
>> That's awesome.
(Russell speaks indistinctly)
>> (whispers): Amanda grabs it
from underneath me and runs over
to the other side of the room,
so I jump up, I grab her and I
hold her arm, and I was, like,
"Give me that ... thing back!"
And I wrestled her to the ground
and ripped it out of her hand.
>> (laughs): Oh, my God!
>> "Follow the path to where you
get water for drinking."
>> It says on the clue something
about a stream where they
drink water.
It's by the stream over here
under a rock, by a bendy tree.
Danielle's looking at one side,
I'm looking at the other side.
I pick up a rock after being
there five seconds-- there it
is.
She turns her back to me.
I take it out, throw it to the
side.
I sit on it.
I-I hid it in my pocket.
I wanted to break away from her
immediately.
Because they hid... they hid an
immunity idol from me.
They didn't let me know about
it.
You know what?
I'm not letting them know about
it.
I am the king of hidden immunity
idols.
(thunder rumbling)
>> It's still raining.
>> Barely.
(thunder crashing)
This is my guarantee to you that
I'm serious and this isn't...
I have the idol.
>> How'd you get it?
>> Because she gave me the clue,
and I found it before she even
got there.
>> Nice!
>> With me showing you the idol,
it should show you that I trust
you 100%.
>> Will you show it to me now?
>> You want to see it now?
>> I'd rather see it now.
>> Okay, let's go see it, then.
>> All right.
>> Stick with me.
I could take you places.
>> Knowing that Russell has the
idol could be a little bit of
ammunition for me, but right now
I can't tell anybody, because I
can't trust anybody to not take
a little bit of information that
they get and use it against me.
>> But now you trust me.
>> I trust you.
>> We are going to the final
three.
This is what's gonna get us
there.
>> I'm not sure that I trust
Russell a hundred percent, but
it's a big thing that he showed
me the hidden immunity idol.
So it's just, it's really tough.
It was a tough decision to make.
>> This is real.
>> All right.
>> Tyson was first-- he was in
my alliance.
Then they took out Boston Rob--
he was in my alliance.
They took out Courtney before we
came here because they knew that
if me and Courtney came over
here, they were done.
>> Okay.
>> So if I flip with you guys
and make it five against four,
it's either got to be Danielle,
Parvati or Russell.
When Tyson went and then Boston
Rob went and then Courtney left
me, I was, like, I'm done.
But now that they took out J.T.
and now I can jump to them and
be five against four, now is the
perfect time for me to make my
move.
>> In terms of the idol, I
agree with you-- Danielle has
it.
>> And she's greedy.
>> I also agree she's not gonna
give it away.
I know Danielle has the hidden
immunity idol, or will, because
she has the clue.
So we have to assume she's gonna
find it and she'll have it in
her possession.
But if Danielle doesn't win
immunity today-- which I'm gonna
try my damndest to keep her from
it-- don't you think she'll play
the idol tonight?
>> She don't think she's in
bad shape.
They won't tell me till, like,
an hour before who it is,
because they don't tell me
nothing.
>> So we need to make sure they
don't think you're flipping.
So the thing is, we need you.
We need you, and if you want to
do this, do we first take out
Russell or Parvati?
Tonight.
>> What, did Colby try to talk
to you any?
>> No. He-he's kind of, like,
uptight.
Like Jerri said, he, like,
doesn't have no personality.
>> Yeah.
>> I know I told you I haven't
talked to him since the day we
got here-- that's why he's dying
to talk to me.
>> We have five votes right now.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> We have six votes.
>> Oh.
>> Like, if you would flip, and
all of a sudden we get five
votes and you vote another
way... that would be...
>> It wouldn't matter.
>> ...bad for the game.
>> No. No. Hold up.
You're doing math wrong.
>> No... no, I'm saying we have
six people.
We have one person from their
tribe voting with us today.
>> Oh, okay.
>> But anyway, I trust you.
(Sandra laughs)
>> If I stay with the Villains,
I'm top five, I'm not moving up
from there-- because they're not
willing to get rid of Russell.
That's why I have to flip to the
Heroes-- because I need to get
Russell out.
Russell? You want Russell gone?
>> Yeah.
>> Russell's gone. He's gone.
>> All four of us are going,
all four of us will vote for...
>> Yeah, but Russell just told
me now, somebody from them
already came to us again.
I'm hoping that one of those
girls is lying, and that
they're gonna stick with you.
They need to stick with you or
this won't work.
If they don't stick with you,
they're going home one after the
other.
So it's up to you.
>> I'd rather...
Which do you want?
I'd rather put Russell's ass
out there.
My gosh, alls it will take is
Sandra to switch over to our
side, there's five votes for
Russell, we could get Russell
out of this game!
The guy is a piece of garbage.
>> Sandra's the one that came to
me.
And then this morning, she just
spilled the beans of why she's
so sick of all of them,
including Russell.
Really wants to get rid of
Russell. Um...
>> So we vote tonight for
whoever she wants?
>> Yeah. I mean, this is it.
So... I don't see any reason why
Sandra would bluff me at this
point.
If Sandra's telling me the
truth.
Who knows, she could be playing
me for the Villains.
But if she's telling me the
truth, you know, she's ready to
come on board and play ball with
us.
So this changes everything, in a
hurry.
So what we've got to do is go
into immunity, try to win to
prevent the Villain from getting
it.
But if we don't, we hope that
Sandra's telling us the truth,
we hope she's gonna vote with
us, and in that case, we will
either vote out Russell or
Parvati tonight.
>> PROBST: Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
>> Yes, sir.
>> PROBST: First things first.
Danielle.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
each have a 150 wooden tiles.
On my go, you will use those
tiles to build a house of cards
ten feet tall.
First person to finish wins
immunity, is guaranteed a
one-in-eight shot at winning
this game.
Losers go to Tribal Council,
where somebody will be voted
out.
We'll draw for spots, we'll
get started.
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go.
First person to get to ten feet
wins immunity.
Very quickly, there are lots of
different strategies about how
to build this.
It's going to take some
experimenting.
You may crash and burn a few
times.
Don't panic if yours crumbles.
Don't panic if you see the
person next to you doing better.
Jerri doing a very nice job.
Russell's doing a nice job.
Building a nice base.
Danielle staying in it.
Colby's building a nice house
of cards.
And it all comes tumbling down.
Jerri just at about six feet.
Russell at five feet.
Danielle at four feet.
Amanda still on her first level.
Sandra's collapses.
Sandra now starting over.
Jerri now getting close to the
eight-foot mark.
>> Oh.
>> PROBST: It's Russell and
Jerri both just under eight
feet.
This is when you have to be very
careful.
Jerri with a few seconds' lead
right now.
Russell's going to have to pick
it up.
Jerri at the nine-foot mark.
This will put her at nine and a
half feet.
Russell at the nine-foot mark.
This will put him at nine and a
half feet.
Nobody else is even close at
this point.
This is neck and neck.
Russell is out of cards.
Trying to make a little pyramid
to get him at ten feet.
Russell's not there.
Russell's going to have to
hustle.
Jerri on her last stack.
Jerri wins immunity!
(Jerri whoops)
By seconds over Russell.
>> Yay!
(Jerri whoops)
Okay.
(Jerri laughs)
>> PROBST: Come on over, Jerri.
>> Yay!
(laughter)
My very first immunity.
>> PROBST: Ever?
>> Ever!
>> PROBST: Congratulations.
>> Yay!
>> PROBST: Came at a good time,
right?
>> It did.
>> PROBST: With this, Jerri is
safe at tonight's Tribal
Council, guaranteed a
one-in-eight shot at winning
this game.
For the rest of you, after 30
days in this game, one of you
going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
I will see you at Tribal.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> I'm voting for Russell
because I've been waiting to
take him down for 30 days.
30 days too long.
It's time for revenge, and this
is for Courtney, Boston Rob,
Tyson, and even Coach, who I
don't care about, but I'll stick
him in there, too.
(bird squawking)
>> I'm having an amazing day.
This is the first time I've ever
had immunity, so I'm just trying
to appreciate and really live in
the extreme high I'm
experiencing right now, 'cause
it feels good.
(Jerri laughs)
I'm swimming in yay.
(laughs)
>> That's good.
You go, girl!
>> My very first immunity!
>> I'm fine with Jerri winning.
Any one of my teammates could
have won it, and I'm fine with
that.
I mean, look at the other side.
Rupert and Colby?
They're done.
They look done.
And Candice thinks I'm going to
take her to the top three.
I haven't really made the
decision yet.
So Amanda is really an
aggressive, strategic player.
She's kind of like Boston Rob
in a girl's body, so she has to
go.
Let's put her name down tonight.
We really ain't got to discuss
much.
>> Yeah, I know.
I know she's working it, you
know?
>> Put her name down tonight.
I guarantee you, she'll have six
votes anyway, but I just want to
make sure that everything's cool
with me and you, with you
putting her name down.
I trust you.
I just, you know, I'm playing
the game like you.
> Listen, I'm-I'm ready to put
her name down.
She has crossed me too many
times...
Going into Tribal, I knew that
either way that I chose could
be really the beginning of the
end for me, because I was going
to make people really mad on
either side, and, uh, you know,
just the fact that Russell had
the immunity idol and could pass
it to anyone made me nervous
about not voting with the
Villains.
And, uh, so, I felt like I had
to go with the plan that was
the most solid.
>> I know I got to pack.
I never went to Tribal Council
and not taken...
>> Yeah. Me, neither.
Me, neither.
>> Since Pearl Islands when I
walked in there thinking I was
safe and went home with nothing.
>> Oh!
>> Nothing.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> The one time I thought I was
safe-- that's the day I went
home.
>> Yeah.
>> We got lucky because
Russell's going home tonight.
Done.
>> Take my turn?
>> Yup.
>> Hmm?
>> Um...
>> Acting like she's crying...
>> Sandra.
(Sandra mumbles)
No. I want to talk to you.
Sit down.
Before Candice gets up there.
I don't know why she's running
up here, but, uh, she said that
you said... you know, putting my
name right now.
You're saying you're going to
vote for me.
>> No, nobody's going to vote
for you.
>> That's what she said was
said.
>> Amanda's going home.
>> An idol's getting played
tonight.
>> I'm not scared, Russell.
>> Nah...
>> Why are you trying to
threaten me?
>> I ain't threatening you.
I'm just saying... I just...
I-I... I believe that Candice
believes that this is her only
option, and, uh, Sandra, the
same thing, and because of that,
they have to make the decision
to get Amanda out of here.
>> Right. Then it does...
>> If you put Amanda's name
tonight, she goes home, period.
>> Yeah, I am.
>> If you put Amanda's name
down.
Either one of you all switch,
then it don't matter.
If you put it, she goes home.
She goes home.
>> But she is going home.
>> Right.
>> If Candice and Sandra flips
on me today, then I go home.
They both would have to have
some kind of genius plan to flip
on me tonight to go to the
Heroes?
The beat-up Heroes?
If they do that, then more power
to 'em.
>> Uh-uh.
>> Candice went and told Russell
every single thing that was
said, including that I was on
board with Rupert, Amanda and
the rest of them, and now we're
screwed, and now they won't
trust us anymore after this.
>> Why are you switching now?
>> She's not.
>> I'm not switching.
>> Listen...
>> You're-You're with us?
>> Yes, she's totally with us.
>> Oh, my God.
We are trying like heck to keep
everybody calm.
>> So we just have to figure
out...
>> I'm not hanging you out to
dry.
>> Listen, we're okay.
Sandra, you're good.
Candice is on our side.
We're voting for Parvati.
>> We're not going to let you
hang out to dry.
None of us will.
>> We're not going to let you
hang out to dry.
We're voting Parvati.
Now, who's going to tell Amanda?
>> I'll tell Amanda.
(Sandra mumbles)
>> We think Russell got wind of
our plan and has convinced
Danielle to give the idol to
him, but the greed inside of her
is going to make her not want to
give it away.
If we vote all for Danielle,
they've still won.
If we vote for Russell, and
Danielle goes to give it away,
they've still won.
So maybe we throw Parvati in
and just vote for her, 'cause
nobody's gotten her on the
radar.
>> So if this thing doesn't
work out...
>> What do you mean, am I gonna
help you?
What do you want me to go to do?
>> Are we going to do this?
>> Yes.
>> Okay, so...
>> Yeah, if this thing doesn't
work, it's Candice's fault.
True or no?
>> No.
>> No, really. I mean, really.
If this doesn't work, then
Candice is the one who spilled
the beans.
>> You got five...
It's insanely crazy right now.
There's three days of scrambling
going on in three minutes.
>> We need to do this.
We need to vote out Parvati, and
we'll be right on track.
If you're scared of Russell,
we'll write his name down.
I promise you.
I bet you 100%, Danielle will
not give him the idol.
The fact that me and you are now
talking like this, we're done
already.
We're freaking done.
Russell, can we just have a
minute, please?
It's like every time I try to
do something, somebody is in my
face.
I can't even do nothing.
It's crazy.
>> The only way we can fix this
is to do what they said, because
they think you're just
jumping ship.
>> You're scared.
And I am jumping ship, and I'm
doing it for you.
I did this for you.
I jumped ship for you.
Why do you tell Russell
everything we talked about?
Why did you run to him?
>> I didn't run to him.
>> Oh, my God. We're done.
Know what, they're going to
bury us.
We can get rid of Amanda later.
If we don't take care of one of
them now...
>> But they have the idol, and
we don't know who it's...
who is gonna...
>> You're going to do this
for real, after I put my neck
on the line for you guys all
day today?
>> Sandra. Sandra.
>> And now everything that we
worked for is about to go down
the tubes?
>> Well, then, I mean...
>> Tell me who you want out,
please.
>> PROBST: Now bring in the
members of our jury.
Coach... Courtney...
and J.T., voted out at the last
Tribal Council.
So, Rupert, after the last
Tribal Council, the Villains
had the number advantage.
So, when you're looking at the
Villains, how do you figure out
who might be vulnerable?
Who might be the one that would
want to flip to improve their
lot?
>> We've been talking about
that for a while.
But for one of the Villains to
jump ship right now, they're
still going to feel like
they're fifth.
So there is no real need for
any of the Villains to do
anything but stay with their
five.
>> PROBST: Sandra, even Rupert,
a Hero, says it's a crazy idea.
>> It's true.
The best bet is just to stay
with those who you're with, you
know?
But some of the Heroes have
talked to me, and I know that
they sense that I'm on the
outside, because even I know
that I'm on the outside within
my own group.
>> PROBST: So, Amanda, how do
you make it appealing to
somebody like Sandra, who would
say, "I'm already fifth with the
group I got here with from the
beginning"?
>> Well, you offer them a
better deal.
>> How do you know the deal that
she's got going on now isn't
the best deal?
>> She might have the best deal.
She's weak in challenges.
She's easy to beat for the vote.
Sounds like somebody I want to
take with me to the jury.
>> But there are so many times
when I feel like I'm not wanted.
You know what I'm saying?
So I have, like, a sense of
frustration within my own
alliance.
>> PROBST: So, Russell, clearly,
it ain't paradise in the
Villain tribe.
>> First of all, the whole team,
we play completely different.
Danielle plays her way.
She's real aggressive.
You know, that's how she plays.
I'm aggressive, too.
And Jerri, she plays a
different way.
She's the calm one of the whole
bunch.
Parvati, she's, you know, the
charming one of the whole bunch.
She plays a different way.
>> What about me?
You didn't include me.
>> Sandra, she's just there
with us.
>> PROBST: That's a big
statement.
>> See? I'm just there.
>> PROBST: So, Rupert, there are
cracks in that fivesome.
>> I wish I would have known
there was distrust before right
now sitting here at Tribal
Council.
>> PROBST: Russell, is one of
the reasons you like how
Danielle plays is that the more
she plays, the less chance she
has of winning?
>> Yeah, I'll tell you what,
she's fighting to get further in
the game.
If she gets further in the
game, I get further in the game.
That's why I was glad she did
go to the reward, because
there's going to be another
clue for the hidden immunity
idol, and she got it.
And she had to be very
aggressive to get it.
>> PROBST: Colby, so what's the
sense about the hidden immunity
idol?
>> Danielle has it.
Yeah, definitely.
That's the consensus on the
Hero tribe.
>> Oh, yes, Danielle's found it.
>> PROBST: Parvati, everybody
thinking Danielle has the idol
might take the heat off of
Danielle.
Now maybe you're vulnerable.
>> Um, yeah, I definitely feel
vulnerable.
I'm just trusting my alliance
to stay with me.
But if somebody flips and they
try to make it interesting,
then I have no protection.
Because I've given my
protection away.
>> PROBST: Russell, if somebody
from the Villains were to flip
to the Heroes, you've got to be
a huge target.
>> You know, unless I find an
idol, I'm gone.
But I take risk in the game.
And if you get caught with your
hand in the cookie jar, you go
home.
But I'm well aware of that, and
I'll take the risk all day long
to get further in the game.
>> PROBST: All right, Jerri, you
have the immunity necklace-- I
assume you're keeping that?
>> Absolutely.
>> PROBST: You cannot vote for
Jerri.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Russell, you're up.
>> You're a very strategic
player, but I believe I know
what's going on tonight, so
I'll be using the idol to get
rid of you.
And I found it, not Danielle.
>> I have to play my game, you
have to play yours.
>> PROBST: I'll go tally the
votes.
If anybody has the hidden
immunity idol and you want to
play it, now would be the time
to do so.
>> You know what, Jeff?
For some reason, I think
somebody has flipped.
And to keep them all honest...
hope I'm doing the right thing
and playing it for myself this
time.
>> PROBST: The rules of Survivor
state that if anybody plays a
hidden immunity idol, then any
votes cast against that person
will not count and the person
with the next highest number of
votes will be sent home.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Amanda.
Two votes Amanda.
Parvati.
Two votes Amanda, one vote
We're tied-- two votes Amanda,
two votes Parvati.
Amanda.
That's three votes Amanda, two
votes Parvati.
Amanda.
That's four votes Amanda, two
votes Parvati.
Parvati.
That's four votes Amanda, three
votes Parvati.
12th person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury...
Amanda.
That's five. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
>> Okay, Jeff, I know you've
been waiting forever to do
this... so just do it. (laughs)
>> PROBST: Amanda, the tribe has
spoken.
>> PROBST: Well, in spite of
the fact that another Hero was
voted out tonight, one thing is
very clear from tonight's Tribal
Council-- the Villains are not
one, big happy family.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
>> PROBST: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> PROBST: Next time on
Survivor...
>> We're set up pretty good.
Five Villains.
But we need to be strong.
>> PROBST: The powerful Villains
alliance...
comes apart at the seams.
>> Don't yell me, Russell.
>> I can't believe you.
>> If she tries to get rid of
either of us, we can easily
blindside her.
>> Do not change your vote
tonight no matter what he says
to you.
>> Bad move, you're going to
be next.
>> I made too many mistakes,
and when you make too many
mistakes in Survivor, you get
booted.
I kind of messed myself up in
the reward when I gave the clue
to Danielle.
I should have kept it.
It would have been kept me in
the game.
I think that was my biggest
mistake.
I think the rest of the game is
going to be absolutely crazy,
and I'm kind of glad I'm not a
part of it, to be honest.