>> Jeff:
PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR,
DID YOU EVER HAVE
ONE OF THOSE DAYS
WHERE EVERYTHING GOES WRONG?
WELCOME TO SASH'S WORLD.
AFTER FOUR WEEKS IN THE JUNGLE,
SASH HAD IT ALL.
>> I LOVE HAVING THE POWER
IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
IN HIS POCKET,
HIS CLOSEST ALLY NAONKA
HAD ANOTHER ONE,
AND THE THIRD PERSON
IN HIS CLIQUE,
PURPLE KELLY,
DID WHATEVER HE SAID.
>> I'M NOT AS WISE
AS SOME OF THESE PEOPLE,
BUT AS LONG
AS I KEEP SASH CLOSE,
I THINK I'LL BE FINE.
>> Jeff: THE SASH TRAIN WAS
IN PERFECT POSITION
TO GO ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
>> I HOLD MORE CHIPS
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
>> Jeff:
AND THEN THE WHEELS CAME OFF.
FIRST NAONKA GAVE HER IDOL
TO CHASE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO MENTION
TOO MUCH ABOUT MY IDOL.
I'M JUST GOING
TO KIND OF LAY LOW,
BUT I'M NOT PLANNING
ON PLAYING IT.
>> Jeff: THEN AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
BOTH NAONKA AND PURPLE KELLY
THREW IN THE TOWEL.
>> I'M GOING TO QUIT.
>> Jeff: THAT MEANS
THE REST OF YOU
JUST MOVED UP TWO NOTCHES
AND DIDN'T HAVE
TO VOTE ANYBODY OUT.
NOW THERE ARE TWO ALLIANCES,
CHASE, HOLLY AND JANE
ON ONE SIDE,
BENRY, FABIO AND DAN
ON THE OTHER.
WANT TO GO?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: GO.
HEAD OUT.
SEVEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> AND THEN THERE WERE SEVEN.
>> YEAH.
>> THERE'S THE FIRE.
IF WE CAN GET THAT STARTED,
YOU GUYS CAN SEE.
WE HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
BECAUSE OF THEM,
SIT THERE AND GET WET
AND NOW HERE WE ARE WET,
AND THEY'RE ALL DRY.
TONIGHT WE HAD A TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND NAONKA AND KELLY
DECIDED TO QUIT.
20 PEOPLE OUT OF HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE GIVEN THIS OPPORTUNITY,
AND 11 DAYS LEFT,
AND THEY WALK OUT.
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> IS THERE AN EGG TODAY?
>> NO.
>> HAVE WE GIVEN HER NAME YET?
>> WE SHOULD NAME HER...
KELLY-NAY.
'CAUSE THEY'RE BOTH CHICKEN.
>> WE'LL HAVE
TO BRING THAT UP AT TRIBAL.
WE NAMED OUR CHICKEN KELLY-NAY,
AFTER YOU CHICKENS.
>> FOR EVERYONE IN THE TRIBE,
LOSING TWO WAS A HUGE PLUS.
PROBABLY THE PERSON
THAT DID NOT BENEFIT THE MOST
WAS ME BECAUSE CHASE,
HE'S ALIGNED TIGHTLY
WITH HOLLY AND JANE,
AND THEN ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE SPECTRUM
IS DAN, FABIO AND BENRY,
WHO HAVE ALSO FORMED
A CLOSE ALLIANCE.
NOW, I HAVE
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL,
SO I STILL THINK THE ODDS
ARE IN MY FAVOR
TO TRY AND MAKE A RUN FOR IT,
BUT IT'S GONNA BE MORE DIFFICULT
THAN WHAT I THOUGHT.
>> YOU KNOW,
ESSENTIALLY WHAT I'M SAYING
IS THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I'M DEFINITELY PLAYING THE IDOL.
I THINK THE IDOL RIGHT NOW
MAY BE PUTTING TARGET
ON MY BACK.
SO WHAT I'D LIKE TO DO
IS JUST GET RID OF IT
AND HOPEFULLY
THAT WILL SHOW EVERYONE
I'M KIND OF LIKE A FREE AGENT
AND WHOEVER WANTS MY VOTE
TO TRY AND GET THEM FURTHER,
IT'S KIND OF UP FOR GRABS
BECAUSE I KNOW PEOPLE ARE TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT,
YOU KNOW,
WHAT THEIR END GAME IS,
BUT I THINK IT'S THE SAFEST MOVE
FOR ME, PERSONALLY,
TO JUST PLAY IT RIGHT NOW.
GET RID OF IT.
I'M NO LONGER A THREAT
TO THE FUTURE,
AND HOPEFULLY THAT WILL KEEP ME
AROUND LONGER.
>> MAKES SENSE.
>> I JUST WANT TO BE UP FRONT.
RIGHT NOW IT'S AN INDIVIDUAL
GAME.
SO I REALLY HAVE TO DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME.
I'M A SWING VOTE.
NO MATTER WHO I ALIGN WITH,
I KNOW I'M GOING TO BE
THE NUMBER-FOUR MAN,
SO PRETTY MUCH MAKE ME
YOUR BEST OFFER,
AND I'LL DECIDE THEN.
>> MY THING IS,
AND I'VE SAID IT
FROM THE BEGINNING,
I WANT TO PLAY THIS GAME
WITH PEOPLE THAT I TRUST,
AND I DID THAT.
YOU KNOW,
I'VE DONE THAT WITH YOU.
I'VE DONE THAT WITH BRENDA.
UNFORTUNATELY WE COULDN'T KEEP
BRENDA IN THE GAME.
WE TALKED ABOUT THAT.
I THINK IT'S DEFINITELY
IN OUR BEST INTEREST
TO GO WITH THE WOMEN,
ABSOLUTELY.
>> RIGHT.
AND, YOU KNOW, THEN,
YOU KNOW, IDEALLY IT COMES DOWN
TO FOUR OF US,
AND I THINK THE ONLY PERSON
THAT COULD BEAT YOU
AT THE END IS JANE.
IF BY SOME REASON,
JANE MAKES IT TO THE END,
YOU STILL TAKE ME,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE.
>> ANOTHER THING THAT YOU'RE
LUCKY ABOUT RIGHT NOW,
YOU AND HOLLY WILL ABSOLUTELY
BE GOING ON SOME SICK REWARDS,
SO YOU KNOW.
>> I HOPE SO.
>> YOU WILL,
'CAUSE YOU MISSED OUT YESTERDAY.
SHE DEFINITELY WILL GO
ON THE NEXT ONE.
>> OH, YEAH, I MEAN,
MY THING IS IF ANYONE WINS NEXT,
I THINK THEY SHOULD TAKE HOLLY
BECAUSE SHE DESERVES IT
THE MOST.
>> I THINK YOU ARE NEXT IN LINE
FOR THE REWARDS.
>> WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> LET'S SHAKE ON IT,
LOOK ME IN THE EYE.
100%.
YOU KNOW I'M GOOD FOR THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> I REALLY NEED A REWARD
RIGHT NOW,
ESPECIALLY SOME FOOD.
I AM LITERALLY STARVING,
AND ASIDE FROM HOLLY,
I'VE GONE THE LONGEST
WITHOUT A FOOD REWARD RECENTLY,
SO I'M KEEPING
MY FINGERS CROSSED
THAT THERE'S SOME FOOD
ON THE HORIZON.
>> Jeff: COME ON, IN GUYS.
DAY 30.
YOU'VE MADE IT 30 DAYS.
NICE WORK, YOU GUYS.
>> THANKS.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
A SECOND CHANCE
TO REVISIT SOME
OF THE CHALLENGES FROM THE PAST.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
ON MY GO YOU'LL RACE
THROUGH A MUD PIT,
THEN DIG THROUGH A PILE
OF HAY TO RETRIEVE A BALL.
YOU'LL BOUNCE THE BALL
OFF A SHIELD INTO A BARREL.
FIRST FOUR PEOPLE
TO GET THEIR BALL
IN THEIR BARREL
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
IN THIS ROUND YOU'LL USE A STICK
TO RETRIEVE A KEY
HANGING OVERHEAD.
THE KEY UNLOCKS A CHEST
THAT CONTAINS FOUR SAND BAGS.
YOU'LL THEN ATTEMPT
TO LAND YOUR SAND BAGS
ON TOP OF A BARREL.
THE FIRST TWO PEOPLE
TO GET ALL THEIR SAND BAGS
ON THE BARREL
MOVE ON TO THE FINAL ROUND.
IN THE FINAL ROUND,
YOU'LL HAVE A PADDLE.
YOU'LL USE IT TO DIG UP
THREE ROPE RINGS.
THE FIRST PERSON TO LAND
ALL THREE RINGS
ON THE TARGET WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> YEP.
>> Jeff: THE WINNING PERSON
WILL LEAVE HERE
AND BE TAKEN
TO A PRIVATE RESORT.
YOU'LL HAVE A BEAUTIFUL MEAL,
HAVE A SHOWER,
GET A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP
AND RETURN TO CAMP
IN THE MORNING
REFRESHED FOR THESE
LAST NINE DAYS.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD,
THE FIRST FOUR MOVE
ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
CHASE THROUGH THE MUD VERY FAST.
FABIO'S OUT.
BENRY'S OUT.
GOT TO FIND YOUR BALL
IN THE HAY.
CHASE HAS HIS QUICKLY.
GOT TO TAKE IT OUT OF THE BAG.
JANE IS NOW THROUGH.
GOT TO FIND THAT BALL
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO BOUNCE IT
OFF THE SHIELD INTO YOUR BARREL.
CHASE SHORT,
FABIO SHORT.
BENRY GIVES IT A SHOT.
CHASE GETS HIS BALL IN.
CHASE IS MOVING ON!
JANE IS MOVING ON.
WE ARE LOOKING FOR TWO MORE.
BENRY MOVING
ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
HOLLY MOVING
ON TO THE NEXT ROUND!
ALL RIGHT.
FOR THE NEXT ROUND, IT IS CHASE,
JANE, BENRY AND HOLLY.
FIRST TWO TO FINISH
MOVE ON TO THE FINAL ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU GOT GET THAT KEY OFF.
CHASE HAS HIS KEY EASILY.
BENRY HAS HIS KEY.
HOLLY AND JANE REALLY STRUGGLING
TO GET THESE KEYS OFF.
CHASE HAS HIS CHEST OPEN
AND HIS SAND BAGS.
GOT TO LAND ALL FOUR SAND BAGS
ON YOUR BARREL.
CHASE LANDS HIS FIRST ONE.
CHASE HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
CHASE HAS THREE BAGS IN A ROW.
BENRY LANDS HIS FIRST BAG.
CHASE HAS FOUR IN A ROW.
CHASE MOVING ON.
BENRY WITH ONE BAG LEFT.
THERE IT IS!
CHASE AND BENRY IN THE FINAL.
>> LIKE A SOFTBALL PITCH, BABY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
WINNER OF THIS WINS REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: YOU GOT TO DIG UP
THREE ROPE RINGS
AND THEN LAND THEM ON THE HOOKS.
FIRST PERSON TO DO IT
GOING TO HAVE A NICE REWARD.
CHASE HAS HIS FIRST ROPE RING.
CHASE HAS HIS SECOND ROPE RING.
CHASE HAS ALL THREE ROPE RINGS.
IT'S LIKE HE'S DONE
THIS CHALLENGE BEFORE.
>> NICE JOB, CHASE.
>> Jeff: HE LANDS HIS FIRST ONE
WITH ONE SHOT,
HIS SECOND ONE
WITH A SECOND SHOT.
JUST MISSES ON THE THIRD.
>> COME ON, CHASE.
HURRY, CHASE!
>> Jeff: CHASE LANDED
HIS FIRST TWO RINGS
WITH TWO TOSSES.
AND THERE'S NUMBER THREE.
CHASE WINS REWARD!
>> GOOD JOB, BOTH YOU GUYS.
GOOD JOB, BENRY.
GOOD JOB, CHASE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CHASE.
>> WANT TO HUG ME JEFF?
>> Jeff: NAH.
CHASE, YOU'RE GOING
TO LEAVE HERE.
YOU'LL BE TAKEN
TO A PRIVATE RESORT,
GET A NICE, BIG MEAL,
GO TO YOUR ROOM, GET A SHOWER,
GET CLEANED UP AND GET
A GOOD NIGHT SLEEP.
PART OF THIS REWARD
INCLUDES BRINGING
TWO PEOPLE WITH YOU.
WHO IS THE FIRST PERSON COMING
WITH YOU?
>> EASY DECISION. HOLLY.
SHE GAVE UP REWARD LAST TIME.
I'M GOING TO TAKE HER.
>> Jeff: HOLLY, COME ON OVER.
>> PLUS IT'S
MY 25TH WEDDING ANNIVERSARY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CHASE.
ONE MORE SPOT.
IN CHOOSING ONE PERSON,
YOU LEAVE FOUR BEHIND.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
I HAVE TO TAKE JANE.
I LOVE YOU GUYS TO DEATH,
AND I APOLOGIZE.
>> Jeff: SASH, DAN,
FABIO, BENRY,
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK THE CAMP.
>> CHASE ACTUALLY SAID TO ME
NEXT REWARD IF HE WINS IT,
HE'S GOING TO TAKE ME ON IT.
RIGHT NOW IT COULD GO
EITHER WAY.
CHASE KNOWS I HAVE AN IDOL,
SO FOR HIM TO MAKE
THAT RISKY OF A MOVE
WHEN YOU HE PROBABLY ALREADY HAS
JANE'S VOTE LOCKED UP,
IS INCREDIBLY STUPID.
>> YEAH, TRUE.
A LITTLE EXTRA ROOM
IN THE SHELTER TONIGHT.
>> DUDE,
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
IT WORKED OUT, MAN.
CHASE PICKED THE TWO
LEAST STRATEGIC PEOPLE
TO GO WITH HIM.
>> WITH CHASE CHOOSING JANE
AND HOLLY TO GO ON THE REWARD,
HE WAS NOT ONLY PROBABLY MAKING
ONE OF THE DUMBEST MOVES
IN THE GAME THUS FAR
BY LEAVING ME,
WHO IS REALLY A WILD CARD,
BACK AT CAMP TO POSSIBLY
MANEUVER MYSELF
WITH THE OTHER ALLIANCE,
BEING BENRY, FABIO AND DAN.
>> I JUST WANT TO BE UP FRONT.
I'M NOT SURE
WHAT YOUR PLANS ARE.
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT
THERE'S A THREE-THREE SPLIT,
AND I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING,
BECAUSE IT'S OBVIOUS
I'M GOING TO BE
THE NUMBER FOUR MAN
ON ANY THREE-PERSON ALLIANCE.
SO, YOU KNOW,
LET'S JUST REALLY THINK
ABOUT IT TODAY
AND SEE WHAT WE CAN DO
TO NOT ONLY GET THEM OFF,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
WHAT WE CAN DO TO MAKE IT
ALL THE WAY TO THE FINAL FOUR.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> IF WE GET THOSE THREE OFF,
US FOUR GO.
>> BUT ONLY THREE OR TWO
MAKE IT TO FINAL TRIBAL,
SO I JUST WANT TO HEAR
YOUR GAME PLAN
AND YOUR STRATEGY.
>> SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING YOU
MIGHT SIDE WITH THEM?
THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS THAT YOU MIGHT SIDE
WITH THEM.
>> HONESTLY, NONE OF YOU
HAVE COME FORWARD
AND TOLD ME YOUR GAME PLAN YET.
>> IT KEEPS CHANGING EVERY DAY.
>> FROM HERE ON OUT,
I WANT YOU TO FEEL FREE
TO TELL ME
WHATEVER YOU WANT INSTEAD OF,
YOU KNOW,
US SAYING ONE THING
AND GOING BACK.
I TRUST EVERYONE HERE.
>> AND WE'RE GOING TO TRUST YOU
TO NOT GO BACK ON YOUR WORD.
>> OF COURSE.
>> WE TRIED TO GET SASH
BACK IN WITH US,
AND WE APPROACHED HIM
AND HE SAID,
"I'M WITH YOU GUYS,
I'M WITH YOU GUYS,
I'M WITH YOU GUYS,"
BUT PEOPLE DON'T TRUST SASH,
AND THEY'RE CRAZY IF THEY DO
AFTER WHAT HE DID
TO HIS OWN RIGHT-HAND GIRL,
AND AFTER WHAT HE DID TO BRENDA
AND AFTER WHAT HE DID TO MARTY.
BUT IF SASH GOES WITH CHASE
AND THE TWO LADIES,
THEY HAVE FOUR.
WE ONLY HAVE THREE.
SO I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO TRUST SASH.
>> WATERMELON.
>> A TOAST.
HERE WE GO.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> TO A WONDERFUL DAY.
THANK YOU, CHASE,
FOR PICKING ME.
OVERNIGHT MASSAGES
WITH THE TWO OLDEST LADIES
LEFT ON SURVIVOR.
HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
>> I'M IN GOOD COMPANY.
>> CHASE WON,
AND I WAS SO MUCH PRAYING
THAT CHASE WOULD PICK ME.
A TIKI HUT!
I ALWAYS WANTED TO LIVE
IN A TIKI HUT.
AREN'T TIKI HUTS AWESOME?
>> THE WAY THE LITTLE TIKI HUT
WAS BUILT
WAS REALLY COOL
BECAUSE WE HAD A LITTLE
OUTSIDE BATHROOM AMENITIES.
WOW, LOOK OUT HERE!
>> LOOK HOW MUCH FREAKING
WEIGHT I'VE LOST.
>> LOOK AT YOUR BEARD.
LOOK HOW SKINNY YOU ARE.
>> I KNOW.
I'M LIKE A RACK OF BONES.
>> SOAP!
>> OH, WOW, LOOK AT THAT.
LOOK AT THAT, AN OUTDOOR SHOWER.
>> I MEAN, IT WAS JUST AWESOME.
>> GO, HOLLY, GO,
HOLLY'S STRIPPING.
GIRL, GO!
>> CHASE PICKED JANE AND ME
TO GO ON THE REWARD,
LEAVING SASH BEHIND.
I JUST KIND OF WENT, OH, NO,
AND I THOUGHT HE MADE
THE WRONG CHOICE.
>> HOLLY, WE GOT TO TALK.
I REALLY SCREWED UP TODAY
PICKING JANE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO LIE,
YOU DID.
>> YOU SHOULD'VE WHISPERED TO ME
OR SOMETHING.
SORRY, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
THE PROBLEM IS NOW
THEY'RE GOING
TO BE GUNNING FOR US.
IF THEY HAVE FOUR,
THEY'RE GOING
TO BE GUNNING FOR THREE OF US.
>> I AGREE.
>> I'M SO STUPID
FOR NOT PICKING SASH.
>> IF HE GOES WITH THAT GROUP,
IT'S GOING TO BE JANE,
YOU AND ME.
THAT'S THE PECKING ORDER
THAT THEY'RE GOING TO GO.
IT'S GOING TO BE
THE THREE OF US
BRIGHT AND EARLY.
WE NEED TO TALK LATER
JUST YOU AND I.
>> I'VE BEEN A LITTLE FLIGHTY
THROUGHOUT THE GAME,
NOT MAKING DECISIONS
AND STICKING WITH THEM,
WHICH COULD COME BACK
TO HURT ME.
IT'S MISTAKES THAT I'M MAKING.
I DON'T NEED TO BE DOING THAT
TOO MUCH
BECAUSE THEN PEOPLE
STOP TRUSTING ME.
NOW SASH IS BACK AT CAMP
WITH BENRY, FABIO AND DAN.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
THEY COULD FORGE ONE UP
AND PICK US OFF ONE BY ONE.
I GOT TO GET BACK
TO CAMP TOMORROW
AND FIGURE OUT
WHERE SASH'S HEAD IS AT.
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO.
>> I LOVE MASSAGES.
>> I'M GOING TO ENJOY
THIS REWARD
WHILE I'M HERE AND TRY
TO DO DAMAGE CONTROL TOMORROW.
>> I DON'T WANT SASH TO THINK
THAT HE CAN GO WITH CHASE.
I WANT, YOU KNOW,
WE DEFINITELY WANT SASH TO THINK
HE HAS NO WAY OF GETTING TO THE
FINAL THREE
IF HE GOES WITH CHASE
AND THOSE GIRLS.
>> TRUST ME,
HE KNOWS WHAT'S GOOD FOR HIM.
>> NOT ONLY ARE HOLLY AND CHASE
A BIG THREAT TO SASH,
NOBODY WANTS TO GO
TO THE FINAL THREE
WITH JANE ANYWAY.
SO I THINK IF SASH WERE SMART,
HE'D MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION
AND JUMP ON BOARD WITH US
AND TAKE HIMSELF A LOT FURTHER
IN THIS GAME.
>> HEY, DINNER.
>> DO YOU GUYS THINK
JANE WILL BE UPSET
WE KILLED HER CHICKEN
AND ATE IT WITHOUT HER?
>> HER CHICKEN?
>> I THINK THE ALLIANCES
WERE REALLY DEFINED TODAY.
WE CAN REALLY USE SASH
TO OUR ADVANTAGE IN THIS GAME.
I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE
ANY CHANCES.
THAT KID HAS BEEN SHIFTY
THIS ENTIRE GAME
AND HASN'T REALLY BEEN ABLE
TO MAKE UP HIS MIND.
SO I HAVE A FEELING
HE'S STILL IN THE SAME BOAT
AND SOMETHING TELLS ME
HE'S A LOT CLOSER TO HOLLY,
JANE AND CHASE THAN DAN,
FABIO AND I.
>> KELLY-NAY.
>> KELLY-NAY NO LONGER.
(FLIES BUZZING)
>> THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO EAT HER.
I MEAN,
THEY GOT ENOUGH RICE HERE
FOR 20 DAYS PROBABLY.
I DID LOVE MY CHICKEN.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO EAT HER.
ANYWAY, I FOUND OUT
WHEN I GOT BACK
THEY DID KILL THE CHICKEN,
SO I MADE HER
A LITTLE MEMORIAL OVER THERE
AND MADE HER A LITTLE CROSS,
A LITTLE HEART SHAPE
OUT OF THE LITTLE SHELLS
FROM THE HERMIT CRABS
THAT I MADE
AND TOLD HER A LITTLE PRAYER
AND CRIED OVER HER
AND WENT DOWN TO THE BEACH
AND WAS SAD FOR A LITTLE BIT.
YOU KNOW, I KNEW
IT WAS GOING TO HAPPEN,
BUT HAD I NOT WON
THAT REWARD CHALLENGE,
I WAS GOING TO TAKE HER DOWN
IN THE WOODS
AND RUN WITH HER AND HIDE.
>> I JUST DON'T TRUST SASH,
YOU GUYS, I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST GONNA BE HONEST
WITH YOU GUYS.
>> WHAT DO WE DO THEN?
>> YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
THESE GUYS WERE TOGETHER
ALL DAY YESTERDAY, ALL NIGHT,
AND NOW THEY'RE TOGETHER.
>> HERE'S WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
WE HAVE TO MAKE HIM THINK
WE TRUST HIM.
WE HAVE TO MAKE HIM THINK,
NO MATTER WHAT,
THAT YOU AND I WILL TAKE HIM
TO THE FINALS AND DROP HER.
WE NEED TO MAKE SASH THINK
100% THAT HE'S...
SEE IF HE'S STILL WITH US,
WHICH HE'LL SAY HE IS,
AND WE'LL FIND OUT
IN THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YEAH, IT WAS
AN UNBELIEVABLE MISTAKE I MADE.
I LEFT SASH BACK AT CAMP,
THE PERSON I COULD TRUST LEAST
BACK AT CAMP
WITH THREE OTHER GUYS
THAT ARE WAITING
TO POUNCE ON HIM.
I COULDN'T HELP IT.
DAMN, THEY'RE ALL TALKING
TO HIM.
I KNEW THEY WERE TALKING TO HIM.
IF SASH GOES WITH THEM,
THEN IT'S GOING TO BE ME,
HOLLY AND JANE
FIGHTING FOR OUR LIVES
AND IT'S GOING TO BE HELL.
IT'S GOING TO BE A FIGHT
TO THE FINISH
IF SASH GOES WITH THEM.
>> LOOK AT THESE
FRESH-LOOKING LADIES.
HOW WAS IT?
>> IT WASN'T EVEN A SHOWER.
>> IT HAD A WATER FAUCET.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
>> I GOT UP FROM THE TABLE,
I GOT UP FROM THE TABLE...
>> CHASE, HOLLY AND JANE
GOT BACK FROM THEIR REWARD,
AND, YOU KNOW,
IT SOUNDS LIKE THEY HAD
A GREAT TIME,
BUT I'M NERVOUS.
I'M NERVOUS.
THERE'S A LOT OF VARIABLES
THAT COULD PLAY
INTO THIS RIGHT NOW
THAT ARE PRETTY DANGEROUS
JUST IN TERMS OF MY NAME BEING
BROUGHT UP
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK
JUST BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHERE I STAND RIGHT NOW.
I'M DEFINITELY
A PHYSICAL THREAT, AS WELL.
>> NO, NO. NOPE.
>> I HAVEN'T TRUSTED BENRY
THIS ENTIRE GAME.
I THINK DAN, BEN AND FABIO
ARE GUNNING FOR JANE,
BUT I ALSO THINK THEY'RE GUNNING
FOR ME, AS WELL.
SO I'M DEFINITELY WORRIED
THAT SASH WOULD LEAVE US
AND GO WITH THOSE GUYS,
BUT I'M GOING TO TRY TO DO
MY DAMN BEST
TO MAKE SURE HE FEELS
REAL GOOD WITH OUR CREW.
>> SORRY I DIDN'T
TAKE YOU YESTERDAY, MAN.
>> OH, NO.
HOLLY DESERVED IT.
WE ALL WOULD HAVE TAKEN HOLLY,
YOU KNOW,
AND I WAS JUST A LITTLE NERVOUS
WHEN YOU BROUGHT JANE WITH YOU,
JUST BECAUSE...
>> I VERY MUCH REGRETTED
NOT TAKING YOU.
>> WELL, I APPRECIATE
YOU SAYING THAT.
>> BUT I WANTED
TO SHOW YOU, TOO,
I TRUST YOU COMING BACK
TO CAMP WITH THE GUYS.
DID THEY TALK TO YOU AT ALL,
BECAUSE I KNEW THEY WERE GOING
TO TRY TO SWAY YOU.
>> YEAH, OF COURSE THEY KNOW
THAT I'M THE SWING VOTE.
>> I JUST KNOW YOU GAVE ME
YOUR WORD THAT YOU WERE WITH US.
>> I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
JUST MOVING FORWARD
THAT WE'RE TRYING TO STAY
AS STRONG AS WE CAN,
BECAUSE IF JANE MAKES IT
TO THE FINAL,
NO MATTER WHO SHE BRINGS,
SHE'S WINNING IT NO MATTER WHAT.
>> I KNOW THAT.
YOU KNOW I KNOW THAT.
BUT MY THING IS,
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT TAKING YOU
TO THE FINAL THREE?
>> YEAH, WHAT I'M SAYING,
WILL YOU SWEAR ON YOUR MOTHER
AND YOUR WONDERFUL FATHER,
I KNOW YOU WOULD NEVER...
WOULD YOU BE WILLING
TO NOT VOTE ME OUT
AND THAT WHETHER
IT'S THE FINAL THREE
OR THE FINAL TWO
THAT YOU WOULD TAKE ME
NO MATTER WHAT?
>> YES.
>> I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
>> WE ALL TALKED ABOUT IT
AND WE WERE NERVOUS SENDING YOU
BACK WITH THE GUYS.
>> I WAS LIKE,
PLEASE DON'T LET THEM TALK HIM
INTO SWITCHING TEAMS.
>> OF COURSE THEY WANT ME
TO JUMP ON BOARD WITH THEM.
>> BENRY TOLD ME HE WANTS
TO KEEP PLAYING THIS GAME
WITH ME
AND THAT HE WANTS FABIO
OUT NEXT.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT...
THAT'S A STRAIGHT-UP LIE.
>> I THINK BENRY SHOULD GO NEXT
BECAUSE HE'S THE MOST
TO WIN IMMUNITY.
YOU SAID EARLIER
YOU DON'T THINK SO, FABIO.
>> WELL, EITHER OR.
IT IS GOING TO DEPEND
ON THE CHALLENGE.
WHAT IF HE WINS
THE CHALLENGE TOMORROW?
>> SASH IS BACK THERE TALKING
TO CHASE AND HOLLY TOGETHER.
>> DANGEROUS?
>> YEP.
BUT OUR PLAN IS DOOMED.
>> YOU KNOW,
IT WAS ORIGINALLY ME, DAN,
FABIO AND SASH
THAT WERE GOING TO GO IN
AND PICK THESE GUYS
OFF ONE BY ONE,
HOLLY, JANE AND CHASE,
BUT YOU CAN'T TRUST SASH.
I DON'T TRUST SASH.
BUT I HAVE
A PRETTY GOOD RELATIONSHIP
WITH MAMA HOLLY,
AND CHASE IS MY BOY
SINCE DAY ONE.
YOU KNOW,
SO WE'LL SEE IF I CAN END UP
CONFIDING IN THEM
AND CREATE MYSELF
A NEW ALLIANCE.
SO I DEFINITELY, YOU KNOW,
I FOUND A WAY TO SAVE MY ASS.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> COME ON DOWN.
>> WE'RE TALKING FABIO.
>> LET'S GET ON THE SAME PAGE.
>> WELL, WE'RE THINKING
YOU TALKED TO HIM EARLIER.
DID YOU TELL HIM?
I THINK FABIO
SHOULD BE THE NEXT.
>> I'M FINE DOING THAT,
AS LONG AS I STAY, DUDE.
JUST KEEP ME IN THE LOOP.
I WANT TO MAKE IT
ONE MORE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> AND JUST LIKE I TOLD
YOU GUYS,
I'M NOT SURE...
>> WOULD YOU VOTE HIM OUT?
>> WELL, HE HAS TO GO EVENTUALLY
IF I WANT TO MAKE IT TO THE END,
SO HOPEFULLY FABIO
DOESN'T WIN INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
THAT'S EXTREMELY DANGEROUS
FOR ME IF HE DOES, OBVIOUSLY.
>> WHY?
>> WELL, I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOUR OBLIGATIONS TO JANE ARE,
BUT I DON'T THINK
ANY OF YOU WANT TO END UP
IN THE TOP THREE WITH JANE.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO EITHER JANE OR FABIO NEXT?
>> I CAME OVER
AND I TALKED TO CHASE AND HOLLY
FOR A LITTLE BIT,
AND, YOU KNOW,
THEY HAVE NO PROBLEM
VOTING OUT FABIO.
I'M NOT SURE IF THEY'RE BEATING
AROUND THE BUSH,
IF THEY WERE TALKING
ABOUT ME WHEN I WAS WALKING UP.
SASH WAS IN ON THE CONVERSATION,
AS WELL,
AND I LET HIM KNOW THAT
AS LONG AS I'M NOT GOING HOME,
YOU KNOW,
I REALLY DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM
VOTING FABIO OUT.
I KNOW IT WOULD BE BREAKING UP
MY ALLIANCE A LITTLE BIT,
BUT IT'S AMAZING.
IT'S CRAZY WHAT A COUPLE HOURS
CAN DO AROUND CAMP.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: JANE,
FIRST THINGS FIRST,
I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU WILL BE ATTACHED
TO A HITCHING RAIL.
ON MY GO,
YOU'LL MANEUVER OVER
AND UNDER THE HITCHING RAIL,
RELEASING ROPE AS YOU GO.
WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAVE
ENOUGH ROPE,
YOU'LL ATTEMPT TO GRAB
A BAG OF GOLD COINS.
THE FIRST THREE TO GET THEIR BAG
OF COINS MOVE ON
TO THE FINAL ROUND.
FOR THE FINAL ROUND,
YOU MUST SOLVE
A GOLD COIN PUZZLE.
THE FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
WINS IMMUNITY,
IS SAFE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
AND GUARANTEED
A ONE IN SIX SHOT
AT WINNING THE MONEY.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST THREE TO GET
THEIR BAG OF GOLD COINS
MOVES ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BENRY AND FABIO
THROWING THEMSELVES
OVER THESE HITCHING RAILS.
SASH RIGHT IN THERE.
WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAVE
ENOUGH ROPE
TO REACH THE GOLD BAG,
GIVE IT A SHOT.
IF YOU'RE WRONG,
YOU GOT TO GO BACK
AND GET MORE ROPE.
GOT TO GET ON TO THE NEXT ROUND
TO HAVE A SHOT AT IMMUNITY
AND ONLY THREE PEOPLE
WILL MOVE ON.
HERE GOES FABIO.
DOES HE HAVE ENOUGH ROPE
TO GET THERE?
PLENTY TO SPARE.
FABIO MOVING ON
TO THE FINAL ROUND.
SASH NOW GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
BENRY NOW GIVING IT A GO.
SASH IS SHORT.
BENRY'S SHORT.
YOU NEED TO PICK IT UP NOW.
THIS IS GOING
TO BE OVER QUICKLY.
JANE NOW HEADING OUT.
DOES SHE HAVE ENOUGH ROPE?
JANE'S GOING TO BE SHORT.
JANE, BENRY AND SASH FIGHTING
FOR THAT SECOND AND THIRD SPOT.
BENRY GIVING IT A GO.
SASH RIGHT BEHIND HIM.
BENRY MOVING ON.
SASH MOVING ON.
ALL RIGHT.
IN THE FINAL ROUND,
BENRY, FABIO, SASH.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
WE HAVE GIVEN YOU THREE STACKS
OF GOLD COINS TO BEGIN WITH.
YOU HAVE TEN OTHER SACKS
OF GOLD COINS
TO FIGURE OUT WHERE THEY GO.
WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED,
YOU WILL HAVE
A RECTANGULAR SHAPE
OF GOLD COINS.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
Y'ALL CAN DO IT.
>> Jeff: BEEN OUT HERE 32 DAYS.
HOW SHARP IS WHATEVER
IS LEFT OF YOUR MIND?
SOME PEOPLE REALLY EXCEL
AT PUZZLES LIKE THIS.
OTHERS, LIKE ME, DO NOT.
BENRY ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> COME ON, BENRY.
YOU CAN DO IT.
>> Jeff: FABIO MAKING
VERY LITTLE PROGRESS.
>> COME ON, FABIO.
>> Jeff: SASH MAKING PROGRESS
ON HIS PUZZLE.
>> COME ON, SASH.
>> SHUT UP.
>> WERE YOU A CHEERLEADER
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THE PUZZLE
IS ALREADY DIFFICULT.
THIS COULD CONCEIVABLY BE
A MILLION DOLLAR CHALLENGE
FOR ONE OF THE THREE OF YOU.
>> MAN, I HAVE NO FREAKING CLUE.
>> Jeff: BENRY ABOUT READY
TO GIVE UP.
FABIO NOW STUDYING SASH'S PUZZLE
LOOKING FOR SOME HELP.
IF SASH IS RIGHT,
HE'S MAKING SOME PROGRESS.
FABIO NOW STARTING
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
FABIO AND SASH
NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
FABIO GETTING CLOSER.
SASH IS VERY CLOSE.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
GOT TO CLOSE THE BOX TO FINISH.
SASH WINS IMMUNITY.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: SASH, COME ON OVER.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> WAY TO GO, SASH.
>> Jeff: SASH GUARANTEED
A ONE IN SIX SHOT
AT WINNING THE MONEY.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU,
AFTER 32 VERY TOUGH DAYS,
ONE OF YOU GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> I PULLED OUT THE WIN TODAY.
IT FEELS GREAT.
RIGHT NOW I'M A TRIPLE THREAT,
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL,
AND I'M
IN THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE.
SO AT THIS POINT,
I'M IN COMPLETE CONTROL.
I CAN'T WAIT
FOR THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL
TO WIN MY MILLION.
>> ALL THAT BRAIN WORK.
>> MY HEAD WAS HURTING
JUST WATCHING YOU GUYS.
>> MOST OF THE CHALLENGES
I'VE BEEN SAND BAGGING,
GOING MAYBE 70%, 80%,
AND NOW I LOOK AT PEOPLE
LIKE BENRY AND FABIO,
WHO HAVE BEEN GOING 110%
EVERY CHALLENGE,
AND THE REASON WHY
THEY PROBABLY WON'T MAKE IT
TO THE FINAL IS BECAUSE THEY ARE
A PHYSICAL THREAT TO WIN
THE FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> WILL YOU LET THEM...
WILL YOU LET ME KNOW
IF MY NAME COMES UP?
>> YEAH.
YES.
>> I JUST GOT
AN UNEASY FEELING THIS MORNING
AND THEN, YOU KNOW,
I JUST THINK THAT CHASE FEELS
THAT HE'S REALLY CLOSE TO BENRY,
SO IF THEY WANTED
TO PULL SOMETHING,
I FEEL LIKE IT WOULD BE ON ME.
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE?
>> YEAH.
>> BECAUSE IF THEY'RE GOING
TO WANT TO DO SOMETHING,
THEY HAVE TO HAVE YOU.
SO YOU'RE GOING
TO HEAR IT EITHER WAY.
YOU CAN LET THEM THINK
YOU'LL GO ALONG
WITH WHAT THEY SAY OR WHATEVER,
BUT PLEASE LET ME KNOW.
>> I'LL GIVE YOU GUYS
THE INSIDE SCOOP.
>> MY INSTINCTS TELL ME
THAT SASH IS STILL A BIT
OF A SWING VOTE,
YOU KNOW, BUT HE'S CLOSER TO ME
THAN ANYBODY ON THE TRIBE,
SO IF HE'S IN THE MIDDLE
OF A SWING VOTE,
AND IT'S MY NAME
ON THE OTHER SIDE,
HE'S GOING TO TELL ME,
I FEEL LIKE.
>> LET'S JUST ASK DAN
WHAT HE WANTS TO DO.
>> I FEEL LIKE SITTING BACK
RIGHT NOW
AND BEING COOL IS PART OF IT,
YOU KNOW?
WE'LL SEE, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S HARD TO TELL AND...
WE'LL SEE, MAN.
>> HEY, MAN.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WHO ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHO ARE YOU THINKING?
>> AS FAR AS I KNOW,
EVERYONE...
EVERYONE HAS BEEN SAYING FABIO.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
>> IT'S EASY THEN.
>> OKAY. YOU GOT IT?
>> I GUESS SO.
RIGHT NOW CHASE AND I ARE
STRINGING ALONG FABIO,
BENRY AND DAN
INTO THINKING DIFFERENT THINGS
OF WHO IS GOING HOME TONIGHT.
RIGHT NOW THE TWO NAMES
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK
ARE FABIO AND BENRY.
MY STOMACH IS MESSED UP.
SO THEY REALLY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON.
I'M GOING TO KEEP THEM GUESSING
UNTIL I FEEL LIKE TELLING THEM,
OR NOT TELLING THEM.
>> JANE. JANE.
>> WHAT UP?
>> DO YOU THINK HE'LL BUY THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> WHY?
>> I THINK IT'S BETTER
TO TELL HIM
THAT WE'RE GOING
TO VOTE OFF HOLLY.
>> I'LL DO WHATEVER.
>> SASH, ARE YOU WILLING
TO DO THAT?
>> HUH?
>> CAN YOU DO THAT?
>> WHAT?
>> JUST CONVINCE FABIO
THAT ME, YOU AND DAN
ARE GOING TO VOTE HOLLY?
>> I FEEL GUILTY FOR LYING,
BUT AS LONG AS IT'S NOT ME GOING
HOME NEXT
AND EVERYBODY AGREES THAT,
YOU KNOW,
THEY'LL VOTE OFF FABIO,
I THINK IT WILL BE PRETTY SIMPLE
TO PITCH TO FABIO
THAT WE WANT TO GET HOLLY
OUT OF HERE,
AND I DON'T THINK HE'LL BUY
THE WHOLE JANE THING
JUST IN TERMS OF CHASE
AND JANE BEING SO CLOSE,
SO AS LONG AS I'M NOT GOING HOME
TONIGHT,
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO STAY HERE FOR ONE MORE NIGHT.
>> SASH SAID
HE WOULD VOTE HOLLY.
DUDE, HE REALIZES
WHAT'S GOOD FOR HIM
IN TERMS OF ALLIANCE-WISE.
>> HOLLY OR JANE?
>> HOLLY.
>> HOLLY?
I'LL VOTE HOLLY.
>> ME, YOU, DAN AND SASH
ARE GOING TO VOTE HOLLY.
>> AND THEN CHASE?
>> I HAVEN'T TALKED TO CHASE.
AS LONG AS US FOUR VOTE HOLLY,
WE'RE GOOD.
>> STICK TO THAT
AND WE DON'T HAVE TO DO
MUCH POLITICKING.
>> THEN THE DAY IS MELLOW.
WE LAY LOW.
>> YEAH, I WAS FEELING
A LITTLE WORRIED EARLIER.
I WASN'T SURE IF MY NAME
WAS BEING THROWN AROUND
OR THIS AND THAT.
IT MADE SENSE FOR THEM TO WANT
TO GET ME OUT, I THOUGHT,
SO I FEEL GOOD ABOUT GETTING
HOLLY OUT, YOU KNOW.
I THINK SHE'S OVERSTAYED
HER WELCOME ALMOST.
SHE'S GETTING A LITTLE BIT...
I'M JUST I'M READY
FOR HER TO GO.
>> READY TO GO
ANOTHER SEVEN DAYS OUT HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> ME TOO.
>> I MEAN...
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'D DO
IF YOU WEREN'T OUT HERE.
YOU REALLY ARE
LIKE A SECOND MOM TO ME.
>> WELL, I'M GOING
TO TELL YOU WHAT,
BEST THING THAT EVER HAPPENED
WAS I GOT PICKED BEFORE.
REALLY.
>> WELL, IT REALLY MEANS
A LOT TO ME
THAT YOU'RE OUT HERE
AND THAT YOU TRUST ME ENOUGH
THAT WE CAN WORK TOGETHER.
SO JUST KNOW
THAT I HAVE YOUR BACK, OKAY?
>> I GOT YOURS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I FEEL REAL GOOD
BECAUSE I THINK
OUR FOUR-WAY ALLIANCE
IS GOING TO STAY STRONG
AND HOPEFULLY OUR FOUR,
WHICH IS CHASE, HOLLY,
SASH AND ME
WILL BE IN THE FINAL FOUR.
>> NOW THAT I KNOW I HAVE CHASE,
YOU AND HOLLY...
>> WE GOT FOUR GOOD PEOPLE.
>> I THINK WE ALL FELL IN PLACE
BECAUSE WE ALL KNOW
THAT WE'RE LOYAL,
SINCERE AND THAT
WE'RE JUST GOOD PEOPLE.
>> YES, YES.
>> YOU CAN'T BACKSTAB SOMEONE
WHO YOU HAVE LOTS OF LOVE FOR.
>> NO.
>> YOU CAN'T BACKSTAB MY MOM,
CAN'T BACKSTAB MY SECOND MOM.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
I REALLY AND TRULY THINK
SASH HAS A GREAT HEART
AND SASH IS NOT GOING TO GO
WITH THEM.
SASH IS GUARANTEED FINAL FOUR
WITH US.
I MEAN, WE'RE NOT GOING
TO VOTE HIM OUT.
FABIO AND BENRY HAVE BEEN
A PHYSICAL THREAT SINCE DAY ONE.
ALWAYS HAVE, ALWAYS WILL.
SO EITHER BENRY OR FABIO
IS GOING HOME TONIGHT.
HOLLY, CHASE AND I,
WE NEVER PLANNED THIS
IN THE BEGINNING.
WE JUST CAME TOGETHER
AND ENDED UP MESHING.
AND IT'S LIKE SPOKES ON A WHEEL.
WE'RE JUST TURNING
THE CLOCK RIGHT NOW.
TURNING THE CLOCK.
AND HOPEFULLY WE'LL GET
TO PICK THEM OFF ONE BY ONE
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT THEY PLANNED
TO DO TO US.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING
IN THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ALINA, MARTY, BRENDA,
AND OUR TWO QUITTERS,
NAONKA AND PURPLE KELLY,
WHO QUIT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE REWARD, CHASE.
PART OF THE REWARD CHALLENGE
WAS CHOOSING TWO PEOPLE
TO GO WITH YOU.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: ON ONE HAND,
GREAT STRATEGIC OPPORTUNITY
TO MAKE A COUPLE OF PEOPLE
VERY HAPPY.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
YOU LEAVE FOUR
OTHER PEOPLE BEHIND.
HOW CONCERNED ARE YOU THAT
THAT CAN WORK AGAINST YOU?
>> I WAS PRETTY CONCERNED
IT WOULD WORK AGAINST ME.
I MEAN, YOU GOT TWO PEOPLE
YOU'RE MAKING HAPPY,
FOUR PEOPLE YOU'RE MAKING MAD.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
BUT I HAD TO CHOOSE TWO PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: CHASE, CONCERNED AT ALL
THAT JUST DUE TO BEING
YOUNG AND FIT
THAT YOU'RE A THREAT RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE YOU COULD
CONCEIVABLY WIN YOUR WAY
TO A SPOT AT THE FINAL?
>> YEAH, I'M A PHYSICAL THREAT,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I HAVEN'T WON
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY YET.
I THINK IT'S CLEAR FABIO,
BENRY AND I
ARE THE THREE BIGGEST
PHYSICAL THREATS HERE.
SO IT'S DEFINITELY SOMETHING
THAT WEIGHS ON YOUR MIND.
GETS YOU A LITTLE BIT NERVOUS.
>> Jeff: BENRY, WHERE ARE YOU AT
IN TERMS OF BEING CONCERNED
YOU'RE TOO MUCH
OF A PHYSICAL THREAT?
>> I'M EXTREMELY CONCERNED.
THERE'S NO DOUBT IN MY MIND
THAT THESE GUYS THINK
I'M A THREAT,
AND IT CONCERNS ME
A LITTLE BIT FOR SURE.
>> Jeff: JANE, WHEN YOU LOOK
AT SOMEBODY LIKE FABIO
AND YOU COMPARE HIM TO YOU
WITH THESE CHALLENGES COMING UP,
HOW BIG OF A TARGET
DO YOU PUT ON HIS BACK?
>> WELL, HE'S DEFINITELY
A LOT STRONGER,
A LOT MORE BUILT,
FASTER,
MAYBE NOT THE SMARTEST ON THE
PUZZLES,
BUT AS FAR AS BEING
A PHYSICAL THREAT,
OH, YEAH,
HE'S A BIG PHYSICAL THREAT.
>> Jeff: FABIO, WHAT DO YOU DO
TO KEEP THE TARGET
OFF YOUR BACK?
YOU CAN'T CHANGE YOUR AGE
OR YOUR PHYSICAL ABILITY.
>> I STAY FRIENDLY
WITH PEOPLE AROUND CAMP.
I TALK TO EVERYBODY.
I MAKE SURE THEY KNOW
THAT I'M PRETTY HONEST AND OPEN.
I HAVE TO TRUST MY ALLIANCE TO,
YOU KNOW,
GET ME FURTHER IN THE GAME
AND THOSE PEOPLE
THAT I HAVE TOLD
THE WHOLE GAME I'VE TRUSTED,
YOU KNOW, WE'LL GO FURTHER
IN THE GAME TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: BENRY, WE'RE GETTING
DOWN TO IT NOW, RIGHT?
THIS IS WHERE THE BIG MOVES
ARE GOING TO HAPPEN.
HOW CONFIDENT ARE YOU
THAT IT WILL SWING YOUR WAY?
>> I'M PRETTY CONFIDENT
THAT IT WILL SWING
MY WAY TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: SASH, GREAT NIGHT
TO HAVE IMMUNITY
AROUND YOUR NECK.
>> IT'S THE FIRST TIME I'VE COME
WITH IMMUNITY AROUND MY NECK.
IT IS A GREAT FEELING.
IT GIVES ME A CLEARER IDEA
COMING INTO TRIBAL.
BECAUSE AS SOON AS YOU HAVE
THIS AROUND YOUR NECK,
IT SEEMS LIKE PEOPLE LIKE
TO TALK TO YOU MORE.
THE MORE PEOPLE TALK TO YOU
IN THIS GAME,
THE BETTER YOU PROBABLY ARE.
>> Jeff: FABIO, DID YOU SEE
PEOPLE APPROACHING SASH?
>> YEAH, I DID, DEFINITELY.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS HANG
AROUND CAMP
AND WATCH WHO GOES OFF
AND TALKS AND THIS AND THAT,
BUT I WASN'T WORRIED.
>> Jeff: HOLLY, DID YOU SEE
PEOPLE APPROACHING SASH TODAY?
>> YES, I DID.
>> Jeff: DOES THAT CONCERN YOU?
>> WELL, I THINK IT
CONCERNS EVERYONE.
>> Jeff: IT DOESN'T
CONCERN FABIO.
HE JUST SAID.
>> WELL, I FEEL SORRY
FOR HIM THEN.
YOU HAVE TO TALK TO PEOPLE.
YOU HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
IF YOU JUST SIT BACK AND WATCH,
YOU MIGHT NOT BE FURTHERING
YOURSELF IN THE GAME.
SO COMMUNICATION IS HUGE.
>> Jeff: WELL,
IT SOUNDS LIKE TONIGHT'S VOTE
WILL DETERMINE WHICH ALLIANCE
HOLDS STRONG
AND WHICH ALLIANCE FALLS APART.
SASH, YOU HAVE THE NECKLACE.
I ASSUME YOU'RE KEEPING IT?
>> I'M GOING TO HOLD ON
TO IT TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: CANNOT VOTE FOR SASH.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DAN, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE HOLLY.
FABIO.
ONE VOTE FABIO.
TWO VOTES FABIO.
ONE VOTE HOLLY.
BENRY.
ONE VOTE BENRY.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES BENRY,
TWO VOTES FABIO,
ONE VOTE HOLLY.
BENRY.
THAT'S THREE VOTES BENRY,
TWO VOTES FABIO,
ONE VOTE HOLLY,
ONE VOTE LEFT.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT
AND THE SIXTH MEMBER
OF OUR JURY:
BENRY.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
BENRY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff:
COMING INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
EVERYBODY TRUSTED
THEIR ALLIANCE.
LEAVING TRIBAL COUNCIL,
NOT SO MUCH.
AND THEREIN LIES THE TRICKY PART
OF ALLIANCES,
REALIZING WHEN YOU CAN
NO LONGER TRUST THEM.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON: SURVIVOR.
COME ON IN GUYS!
WITH ONLY TWO EPISODES LEFT,
THE STAKES ARE HIGHER THAN EVER.
SASH, I'LL TAKE BACK
THE NECKLACE.
AND AT THE CHALLENGE THE WINNERS
GET ENOUGH LUXURY TO KEEP THEM
STRONG UNTIL THE END.
>> OH, MAN.
AND AS FOR THE LOSERS...
THEY WILL BE TAKEN AND EXECUTED.
>> I'M EXTREMELY SURPRISED.
I JUST GOT STRAIGHT BLINDSIDED.
NOT WHAT I WAS EXPECTING COMING
INTO THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I'M DEFINITELY GOING
TO HAVE TO ASSESS
WHO MASTERMINDED THIS IDEA
OF SENDING BENRY HOME.
I GUESS THE OTHER SIX
REMAINING MEMBERS
SEE ME AS A THREAT.
I GUESS I HAVE TO TAKE THAT
SOME WHAT AS A COMPLIMENT.