>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY
ON "SURVIVOR."
YOUNGER TRIBE WINS IMMUNITY!
YOUNGER TRIBE WINS IMMUNITY
AND REWARD!
THE OLDER TRIBE HAD LOST TWO
OF THREE CHALLENGES
AND STRUGGLED AT CAMP.
>> THAT WAS GOING TO WORK
IF IT DIDN'T HIT MY FOOT.
>> WE HAVE NO FOOD AND NO MEANS
OF GETTING IT.
>> Jeff: BUT NONE OF THIS
PHASED MARTY
WHO WAS PRACTICALLY GIDDY
ABOUT BEING THE UNDISPUTED
TRIBE ZVENGALI.
>> THOSE THAT WANT TO PLAY
WITH ME, JUMP ON BOARD.
DO NOT MESS AROUND WITH ME.
I MEAN, I'M PLAYING
THIS GAME FOR REAL.
>> Jeff: AT THE YOUNGER TRIBE,
BRENDA WAS THE MASTERMIND.
>> I HAVE PEOPLE ON MY SIDE
WITHOUT DOING ANYTHING.
>> Jeff: AND HER ALLY, NAONKA,
WAS THE CAMP BULLY.
NAONKA'S MAIN TARGET
WAS KELLY B.,
THE TRIBE MATE
WITH THE ARTIFICIAL LEG.
SHE KNOCKED HER DOWN
AND YELLED AT HER.
>> I DON'T LIKE YOU,
NEVER HAVE LIKED YOU.
>> NAONKA'S PSYCHO.
KELLY B.
NEVER DID ANYTHING TO NAY.
NEVER.
>> STOP!
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE
IN COMPLETE DISARRAY.
WHEN THE OLDER TRIBE LOST
YET ANOTHER CHALLENGE...
YOUNGER TRIBE WINS IMMUNITY
AND REWARD!
JIMMY T. NOMINATED HIMSELF
TO BE LEADER.
>> I'VE BEEN SUCCESSFUL
IN THE PAST,
AND I CAN BE SUCCESSFUL
IN THE FUTURE.
>> HE WANTED TO GET RID OF DAN
AND HOLLY AND JANE AGREED.
>> I THINK THE ONLY PERSON
THAT MIGHT BE IN DANGER
WOULD BE DANNY.
>> Jeff: BUT JIMMY'S POLITICKING
CHALLENGED MARTY'S EGO.
>> I'D LIKE TO TELL MARTY,
YOU PREPPY LITTLE BITCH,
YOU WOULDN'T LAST A MINUTE
IN MY WORLD.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
MARTY LOBBIED HARD
AGAINST JIMMY T.
>> THERE IS ZERO TOLERANCE
FOR PARANOIA,
DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR.
>> Jeff: AND IT WORKED.
JIMMY T., THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW HOLLY AND JANE ARE
IN DEEP TROUBLE.
16 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> MARTY, WHAT DO YOU
NEED HELP WITH?
>> I THINK WE'RE
JUST LOADING UP THE FIRE,
SOME KIND OF SUBSTANTIAL PIECES.
>> I HAD NO IDEA
THAT JIMMY T. WAS GOING TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I WAS SHOCKED.
>> JIMMY T.'S A GOOD GUY.
>> HE'S A REALLY GOOD GUY.
>> HE'S A GOOD GUY.
I DON'T THINK
HE HAS THE EASIEST LIFE.
I THINK HE'S...
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I THINK HE WORKS HARD.
MOST OF THE PEOPLE
THAT I TALKED TO
SAID THEY WERE GOING TO VOTE
FOR THE WEAKEST LINK.
I MEAN, LET'S FACE IT,
PHYSICALLY,
JIMMY T. COULD DO
HAND STANDS OVER DANNY.
AND THEY'RE KEEPING
THE TRIBE STRONG?
IT DOES UPSET ME.
I'M ON THE OUTS AND I KNOW
THAT SOMETHING HAS TO CHANGE.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL LAST NIGHT
WAS A SLAM DUNK.
JIMMY T. WAS VOTED OFF.
SO YOU CAN'T GET COCKY
IN THIS GAME,
BUT I'M IN CONTROL FINALLY.
I'M IN CONTROL OF THIS TRIBE.
SO WE'RE GOOD, MAN.
WE'RE GOOD FOR MINIMUM TWO
TO THREE MORE TRIBALS.
IF YOU CAN SEE TWO TRIBALS AHEAD
IN THIS GAME,
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD,
AND IF YOU CAN SEE IT
WITH THE LEVEL OF CERTAINTY
THAT I HAVE, EVEN BETTER.
JANE AND HOLLY,
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO GO.
IT WOULD TAKE SOMETHING
EXTRAORDINARY,
OFF THE CHARTS,
COMPLETELY WHACKED OUT
TO DISTURB MY PLANS NOW.
>> I'M SO PROUD TO BE
ON MY YOUNG TRIBE.
I MEAN, WE'RE THE BOMB.
MY SOLID FIVE RIGHT NOW
IS MYSELF AND PURPLE KELLY,
BRENDA, CHASE, AND SASH.
WE ARE CONTROLLING
THIS ENTIRE GAME RIGHT NOW.
KELLY B. AND ALINA
ARE THE ONES THAT ARE UP
TO GET VOTED OUT.
I HAVE IT ALL PLANNED IN MY
HEAD, I ALREADY SEE THE WIN.
WE GOT THE TARP,
I HAVE THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
GOT MY HAIR DONE,
GOT MY SHOES CLEAN,
GOT THE NEW FIT.
YOU KNOW, I GOT MY SWAG.
IF I LOOK GOOD, I FEEL GOOD,
I'M GOING TO DO GOOD.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOUNGER TRIBE GETTING
YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW OLDER TRIBE.
JIMMY T. VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> MARTY LOOKS ROUGH.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY
TO GET TO IT FOR TODAY?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
DROP YOUR BUFFS.
>> OH, WOW.
>> Jeff: WE ARE
SWITCHING TRIBES.
>> I'M GOING TO CRY RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: I SEE A LOT
OF SHOCKED FACES, MARTY.
>> HEY, LISTEN,
ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE
IN THIS GAME.
I WAS DEFINITELY
NOT COUNTING ON THIS.
NOT NOW. TOO EARLY.
>> Jeff: JUD,
THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE
CAPTURED A MOMENT OF SHOCK.
>> OH, MAN,
WE WERE ON SUCH A ROLL.
WE JUST WANTED TO KEEP WINNING
AND NOW EVERYTHING
IS BACK UP IN THE AIR.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE GOING TO DRAW
FOR NEW CAPTAINS.
YOU'RE GOING TO REACH IN
AND TAKE A ROCK.
DON'T LOOK.
JUD DOESN'T EVEN WANT TO DRAW.
AND ONE FOR YOU, JILL.
KEEPING YOUR PALMS CLOSED,
TURN THEM FACE UP.
HERE WE GO, REVEAL.
IF YOU HAVE A YELLOW ROCK,
YOU'RE A CAPTAIN.
IF YOU HAVE A BLUE ROCK,
YOU ARE A CAPTAIN.
BRENDA AND HOLLY
ARE THE CAPTAINS.
TAKE A SPOT RIGHT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, BRENDA,
YOU'RE GOING TO CHOOSE
THREE PEOPLE
FROM THE OLDER TRIBE
TO JOIN YOU.
THESE PEOPLE WILL BE
ON YOUR TRIBE.
TO EVEN THINGS UP, HOLLY,
YOU'RE GOING TO PICK
FOUR MEMBERS
FROM THE YOUNGER TRIBE
TO JOIN YOU.
YOU DONE?
ALL RIGHT, TAKE A SPOT BACK
ON YOUR TRIBES.
FROM THE OLDER TRIBE,
JOINING THE YOUNGER TRIBE:
JANE, JILL AND MARTY.
FROM THE YOUNGER TRIBE
JOINING THE OLDER TRIBE:
ALINA, BENRY, CHASE, AND NAONKA.
SWITCH TRIBES.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
>> HI.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BENRY.
>> WELCOME.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> Jeff: HERE ARE
YOUR NEW BUFFS.
YOUNGER TRIBE NO MORE,
YOU ARE NOW LA FLOR.
OLDER TRIBE NO MORE.
YOU ARE NOW ESPADA.
PUT THEM ON.
>> OH, MY GOD, THEY'RE CLEAN.
>> Jeff: OLD VERSUS YOUNG
IS DONE.
MEDALLION OF POWER, DONE.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: IT IS A BRAND-NEW GAME.
IT IS LA FLOR WEARING YELLOW
VERSUS ESPADA WEARING BLUE.
NAONKA, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF YOUR NEW TRIBE?
>> IT'S KIND OF HARD
BECAUSE I'M AWAY FROM MY FAMILY
AND WE GOT REALLY CLOSE
AND I'M GOING TO MISS YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: MARTY,
STILL EARLY IN THIS GAME.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE
OF THIS NEW TRIBE?
>> LISTEN, HOW CAN YOU ARGUE
WITH WINNING, RIGHT?
THESE GUYS HAVE BEEN WINNING,
WINNING, WINNING.
IT'S GOING TO FEEL GOOD
TO BE WITH THE WINNING TRIBE
AND I GOT A SNEAKING SUSPICION
THAT CAMP'S GOING
TO BE KIND OF PLUSH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR FIRST CHALLENGE
AS NEW TRIBES?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: IT'S FOR REWARD.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
TWO MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE
WILL THROW A BALL
THAT WILL ROLL DOWN A WALL
AND BOUNCE AND CHANGE DIRECTION
ALONG THE WAY.
TWO MEMBERS OF THE OTHER TRIBE
MUST WORK TOGETHER
TO CATCH THOSE BALLS.
IF A BALL HITS THE GROUND,
THE OTHER TRIBE SCORES A POINT.
THAT ROUND IS OVER.
WE BRING IN THE NEXT PAIRS.
FIRST TRIBE TO SCORE THREE
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH!
>> OH!
>> OH, BABY, OH, BABY, OH, BABY!
>> Jeff: TWO CHICKENS,
ONE ROOSTER.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH!
>> WRING THAT NECK
ON THAT CHICKEN!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE YOU
A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD,
WE ARE PLAYING TO THREE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> GO ESPADA!
>> LET'S GO, GUYS!
>> Jeff: BENRY AND CHASE
CATCHING FOR ESPADA.
MARTY AND SASH FOR LA FLOR.
YOU'VE GOT TO CATCH THESE BALLS.
IF YOU DROP,
THE OTHER TRIBE SCORES.
>> GOT IT, MARTY!
>> Jeff:
MARTY WITH A GREAT GRAB.
>> LET'S GO, CHASE!
>> GET IT!
>> Jeff: SASH DROPS FOR LA FLOR.
ESPADA SCORES FIRST POINT!
NEXT GROUP OUT.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
IT'S TYRONE AND ALINA CATCHING
FOR ESPADA.
JUD AND JILL CATCHING
FOR LA FLOR.
GOOD CATCH BY ALINA.
TYRONE CATCHES ONE.
FABIO AND JILL WORKING TOGETHER.
NICE CATCHES.
>> GREAT JOB, GUYS!
>> Jeff: HOLLY CAN'T GET IT
UP THE WALL,
COSTING HER TRIBE TIME.
TYRONE DROPS FOR ESPADA.
LA FLOR SCORES!
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
NEXT PAIR BACK IN.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GET IT, GIRL, GET IT!
>> FOCUS, GUYS, FOCUS!
>> GET THEM!
THAT'S RIGHT!
GET THEM!
GET 'EM!
>> MARTY, GET THAT!
ALL RIGHT!
>> I GOT IT!
>> Jeff: MARTY DROPS
FOR LA FLOR.
ESPADA SCORES AND LEADS 2-1.
>> WAY TO BE, WAY TO BE!
>> Jeff: NEXT PAIR,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
ESPADA CAN WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
LA FLOR WOULD LIKE
TO TIE IT UP HERE.
FABIO AND JILL WITH A STRATEGY.
ONE SHORT, ONE DEEP.
TYRONE WITH A GOOD CATCH.
ALINA WITH A GOOD CATCH.
JILL WITH A NICE GRAB.
TYRONE WITH ANOTHER ONE.
GOT A GREAT RALLY GOING.
>> FABIO, JILL, YOU GUYS GOT IT.
>> Jeff: FABIO WITH A CATCH.
ALINA DROPS FOR ESPADA.
WE ARE TIED.
2-2.
WE ARE PLAYING TO THREE.
YOU CAN'T ASK FOR BETTER
THAN THIS.
FIRST CHALLENGE AS NEW TRIBES,
AND IT'S GOING ALL THE WAY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THE WINNER OF THIS POINT,
TWO CHICKENS, ONE ROOSTER
AND A BIG MESSAGE
TO THE OTHER TRIBE.
>> PERFECT!
PERFECT, NAY!
>> MOVE IN.
I GOT THIS SIDE.
>> COME ON, MARTY!
>> GOT IT, MARTY?
>> Jeff: OH,
MARTY WITH A NICE SAVE!
>> OH!
>> GO, GET IT!
>> Jeff: MARTY DROPS
FOR LA FLOR.
ESPADA WINS REWARD!
>> THAT WAS GOOD!
>> THAT WAS SO GOOD!
>> Jeff: ESPADA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
COME GET YOUR REWARD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> BYE, FAM.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LA FLOR,
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> WELCOME HOME, ESPADA!
>> GOOD JOB, WELCOME, MAN!
TODAY WE GOT NEW PEOPLE
IN THE TRIBE.
>> BENRY, NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> IF I HAD IT MY WAY,
I WOULD HAVE LOVED TO STAY
WITH THE OLD TRIBE
BECAUSE I THINK WE HAD
A GOOD LITTLE MACHINE GOING.
BUT ANOTHER DYNAMIC
IS THAT YOU HAVE A LITTLE
PRETTY GIRLS RUNNING AROUND
AND THERE MAY BE
SOME FLIRTATION GOING ON.
>> WE GOT SOME CHICKENS.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SURE, WE GOT TO TALK
ABOUT THAT, TOO.
I SAY WE KEEP THE CHICKEN ALIVE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE
BECAUSE THAT'S GOING
TO PRODUCE EGGS.
I DON'T KNOW THE RATE
THEY PRODUCE EGGS.
SIT DOWN, TAKE A LOAD OFF,
RELAX, GUYS.
WE GOT ALL DAY.
I THINK WE GOT
A PRETTY GOOD SYSTEM.
THE MACHETE, WE TRY TO KEEP
THE MACHETE RIGHT THERE
SO IF ANYBODY'S LOOKING FOR IT
AND IF ANYBODY TAKES IT
JUST YELL OUT
BECAUSE SOMEBODY ELSE
MIGHT BE LOOKING.
HERE'S ANOTHER THING,
WHEN YOU LEAVE,
COME BACK WITH A PIECE OF WOOD.
THAT WAY IT'S ORGANIZED,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> TYRONE IS DEFINITELY
THE LEADER OF THIS TRIBE,
AND AS SOON AS WE CAME IN HERE
HE STARTED TELLING US
THIS GOES HERE
AND THIS GOES HERE
AND YOU'VE GOT TO DO THIS
AND YOU GOT TO DO THAT.
AND IT'S VERY OLDER TRIBE.
>> WE TRY TO KEEP STUFF
AS CLEAN AS POSSIBLE.
IF WE EAT SOMETHING,
WE TRY TO CLEAN THE BOWL OUT,
RINSE IT OUT.
>> IN LA FLOR WE DIDN'T HAVE
ANY RULES
AND I THINK THAT NOW YOU
GOT TYRONE RIGHT NOW, TYRONE...
HE'S TRYING TO TELL EVERYBODY
WHAT TO DO.
>> WE'LL DO WHAT
WE'VE BEEN DOING.
DON'T CHANGE NOTHING,
PRETTY MUCH.
>> DON'T THINK YOU A G.--
WHICH IS A GANGSTER--
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT.
>> YOU TWO REMIND ME OF MY SON,
OUR SON.
AND YOU REMIND ME
OF MY YOUNGEST DAUGHTER.
SO I WAS LIKE, OKAY.
>> PERFECT.
>> WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
>> SOUTH DAKOTA.
>> OH, WOW.
>> GOOD HUNTING THERE.
>> YEAH, THERE'S VERY
GOOD HUNTING.
THIS SWITCH
HAD BEEN PHENOMENAL FOR ME.
I FEEL LIKE I RELATE
TO THE KIDS WELL.
COMING BACK, THE KIDS
WERE VERY RECEPTIVE TO ME,
SO JUST HOPE THAT I CAN
SOME WAY OR ANOTHER
KEEP THEM AND TELL THEM
THAT I'M HONEST TO THEM.
>> I LOVE YOUR ENERGY.
>> YEAH?
I KNOW I...
THAT'S WHAT MY KIDS
ALWAYS SAY, TOO.
THEY'RE LIKE "MOM, YOU CAN DO
THING THINGS WITH US."
>> YOU'RE UPBEAT.
>> GOOD.
I FEEL A CONNECTION WITH BOTH
OF YOU GUYS,
SO THAT'S GOOD, GOOD.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> I THINK I HAVE
A BETTER CHANCE
AT GOING FARTHER AT THIS POINT
WITH THE KIDS
THAN I DO WITH DAN,
EVE AND TD.
SO, STRATEGICALLY,
IF THE KIDS COME TO ME
WITH AN IDEA,
100% I'M ONBOARD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS FEEL.
HOW DID YOU GUYS GO OVER THERE?
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE
I'VE LOST ANYTHING LEAVING.
>> PERFECT.
>> I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
>> I DIDN'T EITHER
BECAUSE I WAS WITH JANE
AND I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE
I WAS IN WITH EVERYBODY ELSE
AND THEY WERE...
AND IT CAME OUT
IN THE VOTE LAST NIGHT.
>> YOU LOST JANE
AND YOU GAINED US.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> SO THAT'S NUMBERS.
>> THERE'S ONLY FOUR OF US HERE
WITH FOUR OF ESPADA.
>> LET'S HANG TOGETHER,
GUYS, OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> THANKS.
>> AND HOLLY WANTS
TO TEAM UP WITH US.
WE'LL HAVE THE NUMBERS TO FIVE.
I'M GOING TO GO WHEREVER
THE NUMBERS GO.
IT'S PRETTY IRONIC
THAT ALINA AND MYSELF
GOT PULLED OVER TO ESPADA.
ALINA AND I'S RELATIONSHIP
HAS CHANGED A WHOLE BUNCH.
SO THIS IS OUR HOME NOW
AND WE HAVE TO MAKE DO
WITH WHAT WE HAVE.
>> HAPPY TO HAVE YOU OVER HERE.
>> WE HAVE ROOM FOR EVERYONE.
>> THIS IS SO EXCITING.
>> THE OLD SWITCHEROO.
I WAS PRETTY STOKED ON HOW
IT WORKED OUT, ACTUALLY.
I WAS DREADING THE SWITC
H BECAUSE I FELT COMFORTABLE
IN THE ORIGINAL LA FLOR TRIBE.
BUT THE WAY IT WORKED OUT
WAS PRETTY RIGHT ON.
WE PICKED UP MARTY,
JILL AND JANE.
WE'RE ALL SUPER COOL
AND NUMBERS WISE LA FLOR TRIBE
ARE 5-3, IT LOOKS GOOD.
>> IT WILL BE GOOD TO FIND OUT
HOW YOU GUYS DO STUFF
SO WE DON'T STEP
ON PEOPLE'S TOES.
WE HAD PROTOCOL
FOR WHO TOOK CARE OF FIRE
AND WATER
AND HOW WE DID THAT STUFF SO...
>> WE HAVE TO WORK IN THIS CAMP.
NO ONE EVER SAT DOWN.
UP 5:30 A.M.
>> NO SLACKERS AT ALL.
SO YOU GUYS, LIKE,
GATHER FIREWOOD AS A TEAM SORT
OF EVERYDAY OR...
>> LAID BACK;
WE DON'T LIKE TROUBLE.
>> WELL, I LIKE THESE KIDS.
I MEAN, THEY KIND OF THINK
LIKE ME,
AND THEY SEEM TO BE
MORE RELAXED,
WHEREAS MY TRIBE WAS ALL ABOUT
SCHEDULE, SCHEDULE, SCHEDULE.
>> THEY SIT AROUND
AND CHATTERBOX AND HAVE TEA.
I WOULD HAVE VOTED MARTY
AND JILL OUT A LONG TIME AGO
IF I COULD HAVE GOT AN ALLIANCE
BECAUSE MARTY AND JILL
HAVE BEEN TIGHT AS TICKS.
ONE HUMPING THE OTHER ONE
ON THE BACK.
I'M TELLING YOU.
>> I WAS GUESSING YOU GUYS HAVE
HAD A SHOT AT IMMUNITY IDOLS.
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN IT.
IT WAS IN THE FRUIT BASKET.
WE GOT IN HERE,
WE WERE ALL EXCITED
AND THEN NAONKA SHOVES KELLY B.
AND JUST GOES FOR THE CLUE
AND GETS IT AND THEN WALKS
DOWN HERE TO READ IT.
>> SHE DIDN'T SHARE IT
WITH EVERYBODY?
>> NO.
>> I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT
WOULD HAVE BEEN KIND OF SIN
THAT YOU WOULD NEVER FORGIVE,
YOU KNOW?
TO HAVE SOMEBODY...
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
WE'RE THE YOUNG TRIBE.
I GUESS WE DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT DOESN'T SEEM TO ME
LIKE THIS TRIBE
HAS HAD A LOT OF LEADERSHIP
AND, FRANKLY, AT ESPADA,
I GOT CONTROL
OF THAT ENTIRE TRIBE
AND NOT NECESSARILY BY BEING
A LEADER BUT BY BEING A PLAYER.
FABIO JUST TOLD ME THAT SOMEBODY
JUST PUSHED SOMEBODY ASIDE,
RAN OFF WITH THE CLUE
TO THE IDOL
AND YOU GUYS LET THAT FLY.
COME ON, GUYS.
THAT WOULD BE, LIKE,
CANCER IN A TRIBE.
>> WE HAD SERIOUS ISSUES,
LIKE...
>> I'M GOING TO TELL YOU GUYS
THE WAY I PLAYED THE GAME
AND JILL WILL SAY THE SAME, TOO.
I HAVEN'T HAD TO LIE TO ANYBODY,
DO ANYTHING THAT'S BEEN
BACK STABBING
SO I WANT TO GET OFF
ON THE RIGHT FOOT WITH YOU GUYS.
I HAVE AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> YEAH?
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> WHOA!
THAT'S AWESOME.
>> RIGHT ON.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS REALLY
IMPORTANT
TO SHOW I HAD THE IDOL.
I KNEW THAT JANE WOULD PROBABLY
TELL THEM I HAD IT
SO WHY NOT PLAY IT UP FRONT
AND TRY TO GET SOMETHING
OUT OF IT.
WE SHARED THE CLUE,
EVERYBODY READ IT.
THAT'S WHY I'M SURPRISED
YOU GUYS...
>> OKAY, OH, OKAY.
>> IF ONE PERSON HAD TAKEN
THE CLUE,
I DON'T KNOW,
I WOULD HAVE TACKLED THEM.
I WOULD HAVE CLUBBED THEM
OVER THE HEAD.
>> I WANTED TO.
>> I THINK MARTY IS SO ARROGANT.
HE JUST WHIPPED OUT
THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
YOU KNOW, "OKAY, NO B.S.,
I HAVE THE IDOL."
AND WE'RE SITTING THERE, LIKE,
WOW, SO IMPRESSED!
BUT IN OUR HEADS WE'RE LIKE,
ARE YOU STUPID?
HE'S COMING INTO OUR HOME,
AND HE'S ALREADY SETTING UP
LIKE HE'S THE KING.
>> WOW!
>> IS THAT A KEY?
>> HE HAS A LOT OF BALLS.
THAT'S THE DUMBEST THING
HE COULD HAVE DONE.
HELLO?
>> EVERY TIME YOU THINK
DAYS CAN'T GET WORSE HERE,
THEY GET WORSE.
CAN'T EVEN GET THE HEAT
FROM THE FIRE WITH THESE WINDS.
>> WE NEED TO GET SOME WOOD
IN THERE NOW.
>> THE RESOURCES
AROUND THIS CAMP
ARE DEFINITELY SLIM.
THEY BUILT THAT SHELTER
RIGHT OFF THE OCEAN.
WE'RE GETTING A CRAZY WIND.
THEY'VE GOT A HIGH ROOF
AND THERE'S NO SHORTAGE
OF RAIN HERE TODAY.
AND, YOU KNOW,
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THERE'S ANY SIGN OF STOPPING.
>> RAIN'S GONNA STOP.
IT'S GOT TO STOP EVENTUALLY.
>> HANG IN THERE, BABY,
IT'S GOING TO BLOW OVER.
>> THIS RAIN OUT HERE
IS HIDEOUS.
I JUST DON'T LIKE THE RAIN
AND I'M JUST WORRIED ABOUT,
LIKE, MY HEAD.
BECAUSE WHEN I'M COLD
AND I'M NOT REALLY DOING
TOO WELL I LOSE IT.
THIS WEATHER IS THE WORST.
IT'S KILLING ME.
I'M HURTING.
LIKE REALLY BAD.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU KNOW IT DEEP DOWN.
NAONKA SEEMS LIKE
A HIGH SCHOOL GIRL.
SHE'S IRRATIONAL AND CRAZY
AND SHE JUST SEEMS LIKE SHE'S
ON HER PERIOD ALL THE TIME.
RAIN IS NOT THAT BIG
OF A DEAL HERE.
WE'RE ON A BEACH.
WE'RE WET ANYWAY.
I MEAN, WHO CARES.
BUT I'M ACTUALLY,
LIKE, RELISHING IN IT.
JUST KEEP CHECKING OUT.
IT'S BETTER FOR ME
IF YOU WANT TO GO HOME
BECAUSE THAT'S JUST ONE LESS
PERSON I HAVE TO BATTLE AGAINST.
>> I'M GLAD SHE CHOSE US
BUT I'M, LIKE, DAMN.
>> I KNOW, WE COULD BE
UNDER A TARP.
I KEEP THINKING THE SAME THING.
>> WE WORKED SO HARD TO GET IT,
AND IT WAS JUST STRIPPED
FROM US.
>> BECAUSE IT'S WET
AND I HAVE NO CLOTHES.
>> YOU HAVE THE REST OF YOUR
LIFE TO BE WARM AND COMFORTABLE.
>> I KNOW.
GOD.
OH, I JUST WANT THIS TO STOP.
>> I'M SCARED.
>> YOU'RE SCARED OF WHAT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA DO THAT,
TRUST US.
YOU WERE TRYING
TO CONVINCE HER NOT TO.
COME HERE.
HEY, SERIOUSLY.
>> THIS IS A LITTLE STORM
RIGHT HERE.
IT WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> YES.
>> THE DAY THAT MY DAD DIED,
I WAS DRIVING HOME,
IT WAS RAINING
THE WHOLE DRIVE AND...
I SWEAR I LOOKED IN
MY REAR-VIEW MIRROR
AND THEN THE DAMN BACK
OF MY TRUCK...
LIKE IN THE BED OF MY TRUCK,
IT LOOKED LIKE A RAINBOW
WAS RIGHT THERE.
AND THEN I TURNED AROUND,
AND I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL MAKE IT THROUGH.
THIS AIN'T NOTHING.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
MARTY, HAD A FEW DAYS
WITH YOUR NEW TRIBE.
FEELING CAMARADERIE?
>> IT'S EASY TO FEEL CAMARADERIE
WHEN YOU HERE
IN THE TAJ MAHAL OF CAMPS.
>> Jeff: SO, JANE,
LIFE GOT A LOT BETTER FOR YOU
WITH THE SWITCH.
>> OH, YEAH, HONEY.
BEING DRY WAS GREAT.
>> Jeff: ALINA,
OPPOSITE FOR YOU?
DID YOU GO FROM GOOD TO BAD?
>> I WOULDN'T SAY WE WENT
TO BAD,
BUT WE BONDED IN A DIFFERENT WAY
AND IT'S BECAUSE WE WERE WET
INSTEAD OF DRY.
>> Jeff: GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
I'LL TAKE BACK IMMUNITY.
ONCE AGAIN,
IMMUNITY IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
THREE MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE
WILL BE STRAPPED
TO A LARGE WHEEL.
THREE OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL SPIN THE WHEEL,
TEMPORARILY CAUSING
THEIR TRIBE MATES
TO GO UNDERWATER.
WHILE SUBMERGED,
YOU'LL TRY TO TAKE
IN A MOUTHFUL OF WATER
THAT YOU WILL THEN SPIT
INTO A SMALL BOWL
WHICH FEEDS A TUBE.
ONCE THE TUBE FILLS UP,
A BALL WILL BE RELEASED.
THE TWO REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL USE THE BALL
TO BREAK TILES.
FIRST TRIBE TO BREAK
ALL FIVE TILES WINS IMMUNITY,
IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE,
LOSERS GO TO TRIBE COUNCIL
WHERE THE FIFTH PERSON
WILL BE VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> Jeff: ON THE WHEEL
FOR LA FLOR,
WE HAVE KELLY B.,
PURPLE KELLY AND BRENDA.
ON THE WHEEL FOR ESPADA,
WE HAVE ALINA, HOLLY, AND YVE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> LET'S GO, ESPADA.
>> Jeff: GOING UNDERWATER TRYING
TO TAKE IN WATER
AND THEN SPIT IT OUT.
HOLLY GETS A LITTLE IN.
BRENDA GETS A LITTLE IN.
THERE'S DEFINITELY
A LEARNING CURVE
TO THIS CHALLENGE.
>> YEAH, DO IT, GIRL!
>> Jeff: BRENDA WITH A NICE BIT
OF WATER.
>> YEAH, YVE!
>> GET IN THE BOWL!
GET IN THE BOWL!
>> GOOD JOB!
>> COME ON, GIRLS!
COME ON, GIRLS!
>> Jeff: SASH, JILL,
MARTY SPINNING FOR LA FLOR.
DAN, NAONKA,
CHASE SPINNING FOR ESPADA.
>> SLOW DOWN A LITTLE.
>> Jeff: ESPADA REALLY
SLOWING DOWN.
LA FLOR'S MOVING TWICE
AS FAST AS ESPADA.
>> GET IN THERE, ALINA.
GOOD JOB!
>> COME ON, LADIES!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: BRENDA WITH
ANOTHER NICE JOB.
>> FASTER!
>> SLOW IT DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
>> Jeff: ESPADA GOING
EVEN SLOWER NOW,
TRYING A DIFFERENT STRATEGY
AND IT'S WORKING.
LA FLOR SPINNING FAST
BUT THEY'RE MISSING THEIR BOWL.
>> SLOW IT DOWN A LITTLE BIT!
>> SLOW US DOWN!
>> YEAH, HOLLY!
>> Jeff: WE'RE VERY CLOSE,
ESPADA WITH A BIT OF A LEAD.
LA FLOR YOU NEED MORE WATER.
>> SPIT HARDER, GIRLS!
SLOW IT DOWN, LA FLOR!
>> ALMOST THERE!
ALMOST THERE!
YEAH!
>> COME ON, THERE YOU GO, GIRL.
>> Jeff: ESPADA GETTING
VERY CLOSE.
ESPADA RELEASES THEIR BALL.
TYRONE AND BENRY NOW
BREAKING TILES FOR ESPADA.
>> COME ON!
>> WE'RE DONE, WE'RE DONE,
WE'RE DONE.
GET HER UP, GET HER UP.
12:00, 12:00, 12:00.
>> COME ON, GIRLS!
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY
WITH A NICE JOB.
KELLY B. WITH A NICE JOB.
LA FLOR RELEASES THEIR BALL.
TYRONE BREAKS
THE FIRST TILE ESPADA.
>> STOP IT.
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> STOP! STOP! STOP!
WHOA, GUYS!
>> LET'S GO, JANE.
>> OKAY, BROKE THAT ONE.
>> Jeff: LA FLOR BREAKS
THEIR FIRST TILE.
>> LET'S GO ESPADA, WE GOT THIS.
>> BENRY, YOU TALK, MAN.
>> Jeff: WE ARE TIED 1-1.
THERE ARE FIVE TILES TO BREAK.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
FABIO CONNECTS FOR LA FLOR.
>> BENRY, YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: BENRY CONNECTS
FOR ESPADA.
WE'RE TIED 2-2.
>> GO, GO, GO, GUYS!
>> GO, FABIO!
>> Jeff: FABIO HITS AGAIN
FOR LA FLOR.
BENRY JUST MISSES.
LA FLOR NOW LEADS 3-2.
THERE ARE FIVE TOTAL.
>> COME ON, JANE!
>> JANE CONNECTS FOR LA FLOR.
LA FLOR HAS ONE TILE LEFT.
>> ONE MORE!
>> BENRY!
>> Jeff: BENRY TRYING TO GET IT
BACK IN FOR ESPADA.
BENRY CONNECTS FOR ESPADA!
IT'S FOUR TILES LA FLOR,
THREE ESPADA.
BENRY BREAKS THE FOURTH TILE
FOR ESPADA.
WE ARE TIED.
>> COME ON, FABIO.
>> YOU CAN DO IT, FABIO.
>> Jeff: FABIO CAN WIN IT
FOR LA FLOR RIGHT HERE.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: JUST MISSES.
>> BENRY, YOU FINISH IT, DUDE.
>> COME ON, BENRY!
>> Jeff: THIS COULD DO IT.
>> FABIO!
>> Jeff: FABIO WINS IT
FOR LA FLOR!
>> YEAH, BABY.
YES!
>> Jeff: WELL, ESPADA WINS
FIRST REWARD
BUT LA FLOR WINS FIRST IMMUNITY.
LA FLOR, CONGRATULATIONS.
NOBODY GOING HOME
FROM YOUR TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ESPADA, NEW TRIBE, SAME RESULT.
TRIBAL COUNCIL
ONCE AGAIN TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> I KNEW THAT WE WERE GOING
TO LOSE.
I FELT IT.
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT A QUITTER
AND I DON'T WANT MY STUDENTS
TO THINK I'M A QUITTER BUT...
I'M JUST GETTING SKINNIER
AND I'M LOSING FAT
AND I THINK I'M DONE.
I REALLY DO THINK I'M DONE.
>> WE LOST THE CHALLENGE TODAY
AND I BELIEVE THAT ESPADA
IS CURSED
BECAUSE HOW YOU GONNA GET
THE PICK OF THE LITTER
AND YOU'RE STILL LOSING?
WE'RE GOING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
IT'S CRAZY BUT I'M NOT NERVOUS
AT ALL ABOUT TRIBAL.
I MADE IT THIS FAR.
IF I CONTINUE GOING,
KUDOS TO ME.
BUT I DON'T CARE.
I REALLY WANT TO GO HOME.
I'M OVER IT.
>> I WANT TO EAT BEFORE TRIBAL.
>> BUT WHAT DO WE HAVE TO EAT?
>> I WANT TO EAT ONE
OF THOSE MOTHERS.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO BREAK THE NECK
OR CUT ITS HEAD OFF?
>> WE'RE THINKING WE NEED
TO BREAK IT.
>> WE'RE GONNA BREAK
THIS CHICKEN'S NECK.
>> THAT'S CONSENSUS?
ARE WE GOING WITH THAT?
I MEAN, IF THAT'S WHAT
Y'ALL WANT TO DO.
I DISAGREE WITH IT, BUT...
>> YOU DO?
>> YEAHM BECAUSE I THINK
WE'RE CUTTING DOWN
OUR EGG PRODUCTION.
>> ONE EGG A DAY, THOUGH.
>> THAT'S JUST MY TAKE ON IT.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE
EVERYBODY WANTED
TO EAT THE CHICKEN
EXCEPT FOR TYRONE.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES IT IS HARD
TO GO AGAINST TYRONE.
TYRONE IS A LITTLE INTIMIDATING,
BUT I THINK WE NEED
TO START STANDING UP TO TYRONE.
>> I'M THINKING KEEP IT.
>> WE CAN VOTE ON IT,
THAT'S ALL.
>> I'M DOWN TO KILLING
AND EAT ONE TODAY.
>> KILL.
KILL IT.
>> IF I HAD IT MY WAY
I SAY WE KEEP THE CHICKEN
BUT WE'RE GOING TO KILL ONE
FOR IMMEDIATE GRATIFICATION
AND AFTER THAT WE'RE GOING
TO BE HUNGRY AGAIN.
BUT I'M NOT GOING AGAINST IT
AND JUST SAY "NO,
THAT AIN'T HAPPENING."
IT WOULDN'T BE SMART TO ROCK
THE BOAT RIGHT NOW.
>> WHOO!
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> I NOTICED AS WE WERE CLEANING
THE CHICKEN
AND AS WE WERE BOILING
THE CHICKEN,
TYRONE, HE STAYED
IN THE BACKGROUND
BECAUSE IT WASN'T HIS WAY,
INSTEAD OF PITCHING IN.
BUT AS SOON AS IT WAS TIME
TO EAT THE CHICKEN,
HE WAS RIGHT THERE.
OH, DOES THAT LOOK GOOD.
>> THAT LOOKS PRETTY DELICIOUS.
>> JUST HAVE EVERYBODY
TAKE SOME.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
>> WE HAD PLENTY OF FOOD
FOR EVERYBODY
AND EVERYBODY TOOK
A MEDIOCRE REGULAR SIZE PORTION.
MEANWHILE YOU HAVE TYRONE
IN THE CORNER
JUST FEASTING AND IT WAS
VERY BLATANTLY OBVIOUS
THAT HE HAD GOTTEN MORE CHICKEN
THAN THE REST OF THE TRIBE
SO HE'S BECOMING MORE
AND MORE OBNOXIOUS BY THE DAY.
>> BUT LOOK OUT
FOR YOUR NEIGHBOR.
LOOK OUT FOR YOUR NEIGHBOR.
>> TYRONE'S, YOU KNOW,
GRANTED,
HE'S A VERY PHYSICAL PLAYER
AND HE COULD BENEFIT US IN SOME
CHALLENGES
IN ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
BUT HE'S NOT THE EASIEST GUY
TO BE ON THE SAME TRIBE WITH
SO I THINK THAT CUTTING HIM
LOOSE TONIGHT
WOULD ABSOLUTELY BRING US
CLOSER TOGETHER,
BUT IT WORRIES ME A BIT.
NAONKA IS HANGING ON
BY A THREAD.
SHE'S STRUGGLING.
SHE ALMOST THREW
THE RED FLAG LAST NIGHT,
AND SHE'S NOT DOING TOO WELL.
I DON'T KNOW IF SHE'S ALL THERE
MENTALLY RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT'S THE SENTIMENT
ON YOUR SIDE?
>> NAY'S NOT IN THIS MENTALLY.
>> FOR SOMEONE
WHO OBVIOUSLY KNOWS
THAT SHE'S, LIKE,
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK,
SHE'S NOT REALLY POLITICKING
A LOT.
SO SHE MIGHT BE KIND OF,
LIKE, LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
AS OF NOW THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE KIND OF THINKING
BECAUSE WE WANT TO KEEP
THE TRIBE STRONG.
>> I WANT TO KEEP
>> EVERYONE AT CAMP IS AWARE
THAT NAONKA HAS HAD
A ROUGH COUPLE DAYS.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE A BIG DEAL.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO SEND NAY HOME.
WE SHOULD BE HAPPY
WE HAVE HOLLY.
MYSELF, CHASE, BENRY AND HOLLY,
WE'RE DEFINITELY IN CONTROL
OF THIS GAME
SO WE HAVE TO DO DECIDE
WHO GOES HOME,
TYRONE OR NAONKA.
I MEAN, I'M JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO SEE
WHAT EVERYBODY ELSE WANTS TO DO.
>> Jeff: ALINA.
BEEN TOGETHER
WITH THIS NEW TRIBE THREE DAYS.
TELL ME ABOUT THE DYNAMICS.
HOW'S EVERYBODY GETTING ALONG?
>> UM, COMING TOGETHER,
IT WAS NICE AT THE BEGINNING,
OBVIOUSLY.
BUT THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS
THE OLD LA FLOR TRIBE,
WE LIVED THE WAY WE LIVED,
WE HAD THE WAY WE DID THINGS,
SO THERE'S A LITTLE BIT
OF TURF WARS.
NOW THAT WE'RE ON ESPADA'S TURF,
WE KIND OF HAVE TO GO
WITH THEIR RULES.
>> Jeff: BENRY, TELL ME
ABOUT LEADERSHIP.
YOU'VE GOT FOUR PEOPLE
FROM THE YOUNG TRIBE,
FOUR PEOPLE
FROM THE OLDER TRIBE.
>> YEAH.
TYRONE SEEMS TO BE THE BOSS MAN
AROUND ESPADA.
HE'S GOT AN ASSERTIVE
PERSONALITY,
A LOUD VOICE,
AND WHAT HE SAYS USUALLY GOES.
>> Jeff: TYRONE?
>> SIR?
>> Jeff: WHAT COMES WITH BEING
THE LEADER OF THIS TRIBE?
>> IT'S A HUGE RESPONSIBILITY
BECAUSE PEOPLE LOOK TO YOU
FOR ANSWERS,
INSIGHT AND WISDOM SO TO SPEAK.
>> Jeff: DO YOU FEEL QUALIFIED?
>> YEAH, I DEFINITELY
FEEL QUALIFIED
TO BE A LEADER OF THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU HAPPY
BEING THE LEADER?
>> YEAH, I EMBRACE THE POSITION.
BASICALLY WHEN I LEAD,
I TAKE INPUT FROM OTHERS.
I DON'T MAKE
UNILATERAL DECISIONS,
SO IT'S INTERESTING THAT ALINA
SAID THERE WERE TURF WARS.
MAYBE WE CAN ADDRESS THEM
BECAUSE I WANT IT TO BE
AS SMOOTH AS IT CAN BE
FOR ALL PARTIES INVOLVED.
>> Jeff: WELL, NOW'S A GOOD TIME
TO ADDRESS THEM.
ALINA, YOU WANT TO SHARE
WITH TYRONE
WHAT TURF WARS
YOU'RE REFERRING TO?
>> JUST WHEN WE CAME INTO CAMP,
IT WAS REALLY LIKE A SPEECH.
LIKE THIS IS HOW THIS GOES.
WE'VE BEEN SURVIVING, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO YOU FELT
A LITTLE LIKE A CHILD?
>> A LITTLE BIT LIKE A CHILD.
>> JEFF, I JUST WANT
TO INTERJECT,
I'M NOT SURE HOW THEY DID IT
AT LA FLOR,
BUT ALL I WAS TRYING TO DO
WAS INTRODUCE THEM.
IT WOULD BE DIFFERENT
IF I WAS LAYING DOWN THE LAW.
SO THAT WASN'T MY INTENT,
IF IT WAS RECEIVED THAT WAY.
I GUESS MAYBE THAT'S
THE GENERATION GAP, YOU KNOW.
SO I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: ALINA, WHAT'S BEEN THE
TOUGHEST DAY OUT HERE SO FAR?
>> I THINK IT'S THE NIGHTS
THAT ARE TOUGH.
ESPECIALLY LAST TWO NIGHTS.
THEY WERE REALLY RAINY.
EVERYBODY WAS DRENCHED
AND IT WAS COLD.
I THINK THAT'S THE TOUGHEST PART
TO GET THROUGH.
>> Jeff: NAONKA, WHAT HAS BEEN
THE DARKEST STORM FOR YOU?
>> OH, MY GOSH.
ULTIMATELY IT WAS LAST NIGHT.
I WAS FREEZING.
I WAS SHAKING.
I NEVER THOUGHT THAT IT WAS
GONNA BE THIS DIFFICULT FOR ME.
>> Jeff: COMPARE IT.
WHAT'S THE MOST DIFFICULT THING
YOU'VE DONE IN LIFE
UP UNTIL NOW?
>> GETTING A DIVORCE AT 26, 27.
THAT'S BEEN THE HARDEST THING
FOR ME.
>> Jeff: AND WHAT WAS DIFFICULT
ABOUT THAT?
>> BLAMING MYSELF,
THAT I WAS PROBABLY THE ONE
THAT MESSED IT UP.
AND THAT WAS TOUGH.
AND I COULDN'T SHIELD MYSELF
FROM THAT PARTICULAR STORM.
HERE I HAVE A SUPPORT SYSTEM
AND I HAVE A SAFETY NET.
AND I DIDN'T HAVE THAT
WHEN I WAS GOING
THROUGH THE DIVORCE.
>> Jeff: THAT'S GOT TO BLOW
YOUR MIND A BIT.
THESE ARE STRANGERS COMPETING
AGAINST YOU
FOR A MILLION DOLLARS
AND YOU RECEIVE MORE LOVE
FROM THEM
THAN YOU DID IN YOUR MOST
PERSONAL RELATIONSHIP.
>> I SURE DID.
AND IT WAS TOUGH
FOR ME TO OPEN UP AND TELL THEM
BUT THEY HAD A LOT
OF ENCOURAGING WORDS.
>> Jeff: SO IT SOUNDS LIKE
THIS WAS A MONUMENTAL NIGHT.
YOU'RE COMPARING IT
TO THE WORST TIME IN YOUR LIFE.
>> I ALMOST WAS READY
TO GIVE UP.
>> Jeff: MEANING YOU WERE
WANTING TO QUIT?
>> I WANTED TO QUIT.
I WANTED TO QUIT
BECAUSE IT GOT THAT TOUGH.
IT WAS NOT 24 HOURS IN THAT DAY,
IT WAS 26 BUT IT FELT LIKE 48.
I WAS AT MY BREAKING POINT
YESTERDAY.
>> Jeff: BENRY, WHEN YOU SEE
NAONKA CLEARLY STRUGGLING,
THERE HAS TO BE
A NURTURING PART OF YOU
WANTING TO COMFORT HER.
AS A COMPETITOR, SEE YA.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, EXACTLY?
>> Jeff: I DON'T BELIEVE
YOU DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE HERE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NOBODY WANTS TO BE VOTED.
THERE'S A WOMAN SAYING "I'LL GO.
NO CHANCE MY NAME
GETS WRITTEN DOWN TONIGHT."
YVE, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT?
>> I THINK I DO.
>> Jeff: YOU THINK YOU DO?
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT, I DO.
WHEN I SEE NAY
START BREAKING DOWN MENTALLY,
IN MY HEAD I DON'T SEE
LONGEVITY THERE
AND I START QUESTIONING IT,
I DO.
WHY ARE YOU HERE IF YOU'RE
STARTING TO BREAK DOWN?
AM I GOING TO ALIGN WITH YOU
AND A WEEK OR TWO
I JUST SEE IT AGAIN?
I WANT LONGEVITY
WITH THESE PEOPLE,
AND IT DID MAKE ME QUESTION.
>> Jeff: NAONKA,
WHILE YOU WERE BREAKING DOWN,
WERE YOU CONSCIOUS ENOUGH OF THE
GAME AROUND YOU TO THINK,
MAN, THIS IS NOT GOOD RIGHT NOW?
>> WELL, EVERYTHING GETS TRICKY
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
MAYBE THERE'S SOME PEOPLE
THAT ARE ZIPPING THEIR LIP.
MAYBE SOME PEOPLE
ARE JUST KEEPING IT 100,
WHICH IS KEEPING IT REAL.
SO I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S A LOT OF SMART PEOPLE
ON THIS TEAM
SO THEY KNOW WHEN TO SHUT UP
AND WHEN TO TALK.
>> Jeff: WELL, SOMEBODY'S QUEST
TO OUTLAST ALL THE REST
IS ABOUT TO COME TO AN END.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ALINA, YOU'RE UP.
>> THIS IS A GROWN FOLKS GAME
AND AS YOU SAY,
YOU'RE KEEPING IT 100.
I'M GOING TO KEEP IT 100.
PEACE OUT.
>> IT'S TIME TO DETHRONE
THE KING OF ESPADA.
BENRY'S HERE, BABY.
MY BAD.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, NAONKA.
TYRONE.
TWO VOTES TYRONE,
ONE VOTE NAONKA.
NAONKA.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES TYRONE,
TWO VOTES NAONKA.
TYRONE.
FOUR VOTES TYRONE,
TWO VOTES NAONKA.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT
OF SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA,
TYRONE.
THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
TYRONE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: WELL, THERE WAS
A LOT OF TALK TONIGHT
ABOUT COMMUNICATING
AND NURTURING.
TYRONE FELT NEITHER.
YOUR FIRST BLIND SIDE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES,
AND HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR,
DAN WANTS A BUS TICKET BACK
TO NEW YORK.
>> Jeff: MARTY BREAKS
OUT HIS SECRET WEAPON.
>> I AM A GRAND MASTER IN CHESS.
>> IT DOES MAKE SENSE, MAN.
>> Jeff: AND LOOK OUT,
HERE COMES ANOTHER TWIST.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NOT WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR TODAY.
>> MY PLAN FOR THIS TRIBE
BY BEING THE LEADER
WAS INITIALLY TO STAY
AS STRONG AS WE COULD.
WE OPERATED ON
A DEMOCRATIC BASIS, BASICALLY,
WHERE EVERYBODY HAD SOME INPUT
AND WHAT HAPPENED
WAS WHEN LA FLOR CAME OVER,
THINGS TURNED AWAY
FROM THE TRIBE ASPECT
AND THAT COULD HAVE BEEN
THEIR STRATEGY FROM THE JUMP.
SO I'M NOT REAL SURPRISED
BECAUSE IT'S A GAME THAT
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN
AND GUESS WHAT?
ANYTHING HAPPENED.