>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY
ON SURVIVOR.
DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE SWITCHING TRIBES.
AFTER A SURPRISE SWITCH,
THE YOUNG AND OLD WERE COMBINED,
BUT ON EACH TRIBE,
THE YOUNG ADOPTED
A FEISTY OLDER MOM
TO GET THE UPPER HAND.
>> I LOVE YOUR ENERGY.
>> Jeff: THE ESPADA YOUTH
PICKED UP HOLLY.
>> 100% I'M ON BOARD.
>> Jeff: AND THE LA FLOR KIDS
PICKED UP JANE.
>> I'M AS THICK
AS PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY
WITH THE YOUNGER LA FLOR TRIBE.
>> Jeff: THAT LEFT EVERYONE ELSE
NORTH OF 40 OUT IN THE COLD.
>> WE'VE BEEN DEALT
A VERY BAD HAND.
>> Jeff:
THEN AN EVEN BIGGER SURPRISE
SENT BOTH TRIBES REELING.
BOTH TRIBES ARE GOING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BOTH TRIBES WILL VOTE SOMEBODY
OUT OF THIS GAME.
AT LA FLOR, BRENDA AND SASH
WERE IN COMPLETE CONTROL.
THEY WANTED TO FLUSH OUT
MARTY'S HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND BLIND-SIDE KELLY B.
>> IF EVERYTHING GOES
ACCORDING TO PLAN,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO KILL
A COUPLE BIRDS WITH ONE STONE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SASH AND BRENDA WERE SURE
THAT MARTY WOULD PLAY HIS IDOL.
IF ANYBODY HAS
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
BUT HE SHOCKED THEM
BY HOLDING ON TO IT.
MARTY'S GAMBLE PAID OFF,
BECAUSE HE KEPT HIS IDOL
AND KELLY B. WENT HOME.
KELLY B., THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW MARTY AND HIS ALLY JILL
ARE TWO AGAINST FIVE.
AT THE ESPADA TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THE YOUTH HAD TO DECIDE
BETWEEN YVE, WHOSE STRENGTH
COULD HELP THEM IN CHALLENGES,
OR DAN, WHO, BECAUSE OF HIS BAD
KNEE, WOULD NEVER BE A THREAT.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
IN THE END,
YVE'S STRENGTH WAS HER UNDOING.
YVE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
13 ARE LEFT--
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
(\CROWING\)
>> OH...! WHAT A DAY.
>> 13 LEFT.
>> THANK YOU, HONEY.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> ALL RIGHT, I NEED A...
>> WE LOVE YOU, DAN.
>> THEY USED TO CALL JOHN GOTTI
"THE TEFLON DON,"
BECAUSE EVERY TIME THEY'D TRY
AND GET HIM ON SOMETHING,
IT COULD NEVER STICK.
SO I FEEL LIKE TEFLON DAN.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WE DISCUSSED THE ORIGINAL PLAN
AND VOTE YVE OUT TONIGHT,
BUT I'M A LITTLE BIT WORRIED
ABOUT DAN'S PERFORMANCE.
IT'LL DEFINITELY BE
A HARD PILL TO SWALLOW
IF DAN COSTS US THE CHALLENGES.
BUT WE'VE MADE OUR DECISIONS,
WE'VE MADE OUR BEDS,
AND WE'VE GOT TO LAY IN IT.
>> ALINA IS STRONG
AND SHE'S VERY SMART.
FROM DAY ONE,
SHE HAD THESE EYES
THAT CAN JUST SEE
STRAIGHT THROUGH YOU.
I NEVER TRUSTED HER AT ALL.
SO WE NEED
TO GET ALINA OUT NEXT.
AND THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> ALL RIGHT?
>> OKAY.
>> COULD I JUST SAY, WOW! WOW!
>> WE WOULD'VE GONE
WITH WHATEVER
YOU GUYS WOULD HAVE SAID.
>> WE WANTED TO FLUSH THE IDOL,
WAS THE PLAN BUT...
>> WHY ANY VOTES ON ME?
WHAT WERE THE VOTES ON ME?
WHAT WAS THAT?
>> YOU HAVE THE IDOL.
>> YOU GOT TO HAVE
BIG, BIG CAJONES
TO PULL THE MOVE
THAT I PULLED TONIGHT,
WHICH IS, I DID NOT PLAY
THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
I SENSED THAT YOU GUYS
WANTED TO FLUSH THE IDOL,
BUT SOMETHING IN MY GUT SAID
THAT THAT WASN'T
TOTALLY BULL ... SO...
I KEPT THAT IMMUNITY IDOL
IN MY POCKET,
AND I DEBATED LONG AND HARD,
AND SOMETHING TOLD ME
HANG ON TO IT, AND I WAS RIGHT.
I ALSO NEED TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF JANE.
OBVIOUSLY,
JANE VOTED FOR ME TONIGHT,
SO THAT'S GOING TO HAVE
TO BE DEALT WITH.
I'M JUST SITTING HERE
SEETHING ABOUT JANE, ACTUALLY.
I HAVE NEVER LIED TO HER ONCE,
I HAVE NEVER MISLED HER,
I'VE NEVER VOTED FOR HER.
SHE TURNED ON ME.
SHE'S A DESPERATE ONE AND SHE
HAS BEEN FROM THE BEGINNING,
AND SHE'S GOT TO GO.
>> SHE'S NEXT.
>> SHE'S PISSING ME OFF.
>> HEY, THE ONE THING
I WANTED TO SAY
AFTER LAST NIGHT TO YOU IS...
ACTUALLY, LIKE, THREE THINGS.
ONE IS...
I HAVE NEVER, EVER LIED TO YOU.
UNLESS YOU TELL ME RIGHT NOW YOU
THINK I'VE LIED ABOUT SOMETHING,
I'LL SET IT STRAIGHT RIGHT NOW.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU'VE LIED.
>> I HAVE NEVER...
I HAVE NEVER,
EVER ONCE LIED TO YOU.
I'VE NEVER MISREPRESENTED MYSELF
TO YOU IN THIS GAME,
NOT EVEN ONCE.
I HAVE NEVER WRITTEN
YOUR NAME DOWN,
AND I HAVE NEVER, EVER SUGGESTED
THAT YOUR NAME SHOULD GO DOWN.
THEY ALL TOLD US YOU WERE GOING,
BUT WHEN I SAW EVERYTHING TURN,
THAT'S WHY I TURNED TO YOU
AND SAID, "VOTE FOR BRENDA,"
'CAUSE I WAS, LIKE, THIS
WHOLE THING IS GOING HAYWIRE.
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHERE IT WAS GOING.
I FELT LIKE
THEY HAD TURNED ON US.
SO I'M NOT REALLY CLEAR
ON WHAT ALL THEIR STRATEGY WAS.
I THINK THEY WANTED
TO FLUSH THE IDOL OUT.
TWO, THEY WANTED TO GET RID OF
KELLY B., BUT THEY WERE WORRIED
THAT KELLY B.
HAD MAYBE COME AND TALKED TO US
AND THAT WE WOULD USE KELLY B.
TO FLIP ON THEM.
>> BE A FOURSOME.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND WE HAD NO IDEA,
I NEVER, EVER HAD A CLUE.
>> I NEVER HAD A CLUE.
NOT AN IOTA.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I WANT TO KNOW THAT,
'CAUSE I DON'T THINK
YOU VOTED FOR BRENDA
AND I THINK YOU WROTE
MY NAME DOWN LAST NIGHT, SO...
(\LAUGHING\)
>> YOU DID?
>> YEAH, I WAS, LIKE,
"I HAVE NEVER WRITTEN
YOUR NAME DOWN, EVER."
>> KELLY B. GOING HOME
BUYS MARTY AND I
ANOTHER THREE DAYS HERE.
I'M HOPING THAT
JANE WILL BE NEXT,
BUT MARTY AND I ARE REALLY,
LIKE, SCRAMBLING AROUND
FROM BEHIND THE EIGHT BALL
TO TRY AND STAY HERE.
I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S GOING TO WORK.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
LA FLOR GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW ESPADA TRIBE.
YVE VOTED OUT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff:
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
ONE MEMBER OF EACH TRIBE
WILL BE YOUR DEFENDER.
THEY'LL BE STANDING ON A PERCH
IN THE WATER,
WHILE, ONE AT A TIME,
MEMBERS OF THE OTHER TRIBE
LEAP OFF A PLATFORM
AND ATTEMPT TO THROW A BALL
PAST THE DEFENDER INTO THE NET.
EACH TIME YOU GET
A BALL IN THE NET,
YOU SCORE A POINT
FOR YOUR TRIBE.
FIRST TRIBE TO SCORE FIVE POINTS
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TOMORROW MORNING
THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL ENJOY
A NICARAGUAN FARM EXPERIENCE.
THAT INCLUDES
A LITTLE HORSEBACK RIDING
AND THE MAKING
OF A FRESH BREAKFAST
WITH TORTILLAS...
EGGS, CHEESE,
AND FRESH MILK
THAT YOU GUYS WILL COLLECT
FROM THE COW YOURSELVES.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LA FLOR,
YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA MEMBER,
SITTING ONE PERSON OUT.
CANNOT SIT OUT
THE SAME PERSON
IN BACK-TO-BACK CHALLENGES.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> JANE.
>> Jeff: JANE, TAKE A SPOT
ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL GIVE YOU
A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE
AND DECIDE WHO
YOUR DEFENDER'S GOING TO BE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
OKAY, WE HAVE OUR TWO DEFENDERS.
FABIO FOR LA FLOR,
CHASE FOR ESPADA.
ESPADA WON
THE ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS.
THEY'RE UP FIRST.
HERE WE GO.
NAONKA TAKING ON FABIO.
LOOKING FOR THE FIRST POINT
IN THIS GAME.
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
ESPADA SCORES!
ESPADA LEADS ONE-ZIP.
>> YOU GOT A PIECE OF IT, FABIO,
YOU GOT A PIECE OF IT, MAN.
>> Jeff: NEXT ROUND,
IT IS JILL FOR LA FLOR
TAKING ON CHASE.
JILL LOOKING TO TIE IT UP.
AND SHE DOES!
WE ARE TIED ONE-ONE.
BENRY NOW UP FOR ESPADA.
GOING UP AGAINST FABIO.
BENRY COULD PUT ESPADA AHEAD.
BENRY SCORES FOR ESPADA
WITH A DOUBLE FAKE-OUT!
>> THAT'S A GOOD MOVE, GUYS.
REMEMBER THAT ONE.
>> Jeff: ESPADA LEADS TWO-ONE.
WE ARE PLAYING TO FIVE.
IT IS MARTY FROM LA FLOR
GOING UP AGAINST CHASE.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: OH, MARTY!
THROWS HARD...
AND HITS CHASE IN THE SPOT
NO GUY WANTS TO BE HIT.
NO SCORE FOR LA FLOR.
UP FOR ESPADA, HOLLY.
GOING UP AGAINST FABIO.
NICE DEFLECTION FROM FABIO.
NO SCORE THAT ROUND.
ESPADA LEADS TWO-ONE.
NEXT ROUND, IT IS PURPLE KELLY
UP FOR LA FLOR TAKING ON CHASE.
PURPLE KELLY SCORES OVER CHASE!
WE ARE TIED TWO-TWO!
NEXT ROUND,
IT IS DAN TAKING ON FABIO.
NO SCORE FOR ESPADA.
DAN, IT WILL NOT COUNT
IF YOU THROW IT
FROM THE LINE AND THEN JUMP.
>> HE CAN'T JUMP, EITHER.
>> Jeff: NEXT ROUND,
SASH IS UP FOR LA FLOR.
CHASE BACK IN THE WATER
FOR ESPADA.
>> COME ON, CHASE,
YOU'RE A WALL.
>> COME ON, SASH!
>> Jeff: OH!
JUST MISSES!
NO SCORE.
NEXT ROUND,
IT IS ALINA FOR ESPADA
GOING UP AGAINST FABIO.
ALINA LAUNCHES ONE
RIGHT OVER FABIO!
ESPADA NOW LEADS THREE-TWO.
>> GREAT JOB, GIRL.
>> BEAUTIFUL.
>> IT IS BRENDA FROM LA FLOR
TAKING ON CHASE FROM ESPADA.
BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
>> COME ON, BRENDA!
>> Jeff:
BRENDA UP AND OVER CHASE,
BUT JUST MISSES.
NO SCORE FOR LA FLOR.
>> JUST MISSED.
>> Jeff: ESPADA LEADS THREE-TWO.
FABIO BACK IN THE WATER.
>> ALMOST ROLLED IN, BRENDA.
HIT THE BOTTOM
AND ALMOST WENT IN.
>> Jeff: FABIO,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING RIGHT NOW?
>> I'M GETTING
ON THE PEDESTAL, JEFF.
>> Jeff: WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
>> I WAS USING THE RESTROOM.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: IN THE POOL?
>> THE WATER'S SO DIRTY ANYWAYS.
LOOK AT IT. I MEAN,
DOESN'T EVERYBODY
PEE IN THE POOL?
>> Jeff: I DON'T KNOW,
DOES EVERYBODY PEE IN THE POOL?
>> NO.
>> NO!
>> I GOT TO CONCENTRATE, OKAY?
YOU CAN'T CONCENTRATE
WHEN YOU GOTTA PEE.
>> FABIO IS FULLY RELIEVED NOW.
HE IS READY TO DEFEND
AGAINST NAONKA.
>> COME ON, MAN.
>> COME ON, FABIO.
>> Jeff: NAONKA
SCORES FOR ESPADA!
ESPADA LEADS FOUR-TWO!
NEXT ROUND,
IT IS JILL FROM LA FLOR
TAKING ON CHASE.
JILL NEEDS TO SCORE HERE
FOR LA FLOR.
AND SHE DOES!
LA FLOR SCORES.
IT IS NOW THREE-FOUR.
BENRY UP FOR ESPADA.
GOING UP AGAINST FABIO.
ESPADA LEADS FOUR-THREE.
WE ARE PLAYING TO FIVE.
YOU SCORE HERE, BENRY,
IT'S OVER.
BENRY SCORES FOR ESPADA!
ESPADA WINS REWARD!
>> YES! YES! YES!
>> WHAT A SHOT!
>> I LOVE YOU, DUDE!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
ESPADA, CONGRATULATIONS.
TOMORROW MORNING, NICE REWARD.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> MAN, I LOVE
HORSEBACK RIDING, TOO.
>> ME, TOO!
>> Jeff: LA FLOR, NICE EFFORT,
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> REWARD WAS FOR
A HORSEBACK RIDE AND BREAKFAST,
AND... YOU GET TO MILK
YOUR OWN MILK, I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW
IF THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU GET TO MILK
YOUR OWN MILK, AND...
THAT SOUNDS AMAZING.
WE SHOULD HAVE WON.
AND WE SHOULD BE GOING,
'CAUSE THAT IS AMAZING.
>> WE LOST THE REWARD,
BUT IT MAKES YOU GET UP
AND DO THINGS AND KEEP GOING,
AND THE WORD "QUIT"
IS NOT IN MY VOCABULARY.
I MEAN, I GO AT IT ALL DAY LONG.
I'M A FARMER GIRL
AND FARMER GIRLS HAVE
A STRONG HEART
AND A STRONG WILL.
I CAN DO A WHOLE LOT MORE
THAN MARTY AND JILL
EVER THOUGHT I COULD DO,
SO I'M TRYING TO STAY
IN THE GOOD GRACES
OF THE FOUR TRIBE MEMBERS
THAT I HAVE MADE FRIENDS WITH
OVER AT THE LA FLOR TEAM.
SO, YOU KNOW, THEY CAN
LOUNGE AROUND, THAT'S OKAY,
AS LONG AS THEY FEEL
I'M IMPORTANT.
>> I DON'T CARE
WHAT THEY DO RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT GOING
TO TELL THEM TO GET OFF THEIR...
LAZY LITTLE ASSES.
LET THEM SLEEP.
LET THEM SLEEP, LET THEM RELAX.
AS LONG AS WE WIN CHALLENGES,
THAT'S ALL I CARE ABOUT.
>> YOU KNOW, SHE'S A MASTER
FISHER WOMAN, SO HOPEFULLY...
>> THE OLDER PEOPLE
WHO CAME OVER FROM ESPADA
CAN WORK THEIR BUTTS OFF,
FEED ME ALL DAY LONG,
AND, YOU KNOW,
THEY'LL HELP ME GET STRONGER,
SO I LOVE IT. UM...
YOU KNOW, I GET TO STAY HOME
ALL DAY, RELAX,
EAT THE FRUITS OF THEIR LABOR,
WHILE THEY GO OUT,
THEY WORK HARD.
YOU KNOW,
I GIVE THEM A LOT OF CREDIT,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS A GAME AND, YOU KNOW,
LONG RUN... FOR ME,
WHO STAYS IN THIS GAME
ISN'T A MATTER OF HOW HARD
YOU WORK AROUND CAMP,
IT'S ABOUT HOW LOYAL
YOU ARE TO ME.
>> HOPEFULLY...
FINGERS CROSSED,
WE'LL GET FISH TODAY.
>> WE WON REWARD
AND WE SHOWED UP, AND...
IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
I MEAN, I GREW UP
ON A HORSE FARM IN FLORIDA,
AND SINCE MY DAD PASSED AWAY,
WE STOPPED HAVING ANY HORSES
IN OUR BARN, AND THAT
WAS JUST AMAZING FOR ME,
ALL THE EMOTIONS AND EVERYTHING.
YOU GET A LOT OF TIME
TO REFLECT ON...
STUFF THAT YOU MISSED, AND I
REALLY, REALLY MISS MY DAD.
JUST BEING HERE,
THE FIRST REWARD THAT I GET
WAS BEING ABLE TO SPEND IT
ON A HORSE,
WHICH WAS JUST UNBELIEVABLE,
'CAUSE IT JUST REMINDED ME,
LIKE, GOD, HE'S JUST HERE,
HE'S WITH ME.
AND IT WAS JUST AN UNBELIEVABLE
FEELING, 'CAUSE...
YOU KNOW, I MISS MY DAD, AND...
>> HEY, THAT WAS AWESOME!
>> YEAH!
>> THAT'S WHY WE'RE
GONNA KEEP WINNING.
(\COW MOOS\)
>> WELCOME TO OUR FARM.
FIRST THING WE'RE GOING TO DO
IS MILK THE COW.
IT'S REALLY EASY, BUT PROBABLY
YOU HAVEN'T TRIED BEFORE.
>> NEVER.
>> OKAY, WHAT YOU DO IS,
PRESS ON THE TOP,
AND THEN YOU SQUEEZE DOWN.
SO, WHO WANT TO TRY FIRST?
>> HERE GOES NOTHING.
>> LET'S GO.
>> COME ON, DAN!
>> I THINK I WAS...
I THINK I WENT OUT
ON A DATE WITH HER.
(\LAUGHTER\)
(\COW MOOS\)
>> WHOA!
>> I GOT IT!
>> ALL RIGHT, NAY,
GIVE IT A SHOT.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT, NAY.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
>> OH, WOW,
THEY FEEL SO SWOLLEN.
>> WHOA, NAY.
(\INDISTINCT TALKING, LAUGHING\)
>> YOU CAN DO IT, NAY.
YOU CAN DO IT.
>> NAY'S NOT A FARM GIRL.
>> LET ME DO IT WITH YOUR HAND.
(\CHEERING\)
I AM NOT A FARM PERSON.
I DON'T MILK ANIMALS.
I DON'T PLAY WITH ANIMALS'
NIPPLES TRYING TO GET MILK OUT.
OKAY, I'M OVER IT.
BUT IT WAS OKAY,
'CAUSE I COULD SAY THAT
I TOUCHED A COW'S NIPPLE.
(\COW MOOS\)
>> YES!
IT WORKED! WHOO!
HE WHO DOESN'T FISH WITH ME
SHOULDN'T GET ALL THE RICHES.
(\LAUGHS\)
I'VE BEEN UP SINCE 5:30,
WORKING ALL DAY TO CATCH FISH.
I'M STARVING.
I WANT ME A FISH.
I'M GONNA EAT THIS ONE
I JUST CAUGHT.
I THINK I DESERVE IT.
(\LAUGHS\)
BUT IF I'M GOING
TO COOK THIS SUCKER,
I GOT TO GO HIDE IN THE WOODS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW SAFE THAT IS
AT THE MOMENT,
BUT I'M GOING TO TRY.
(\MONKEYS GRUNTING\)
>> THEY'RE GOING TO BE
WONDERING WHERE I'M AT.
NEVER COOKED
A CATFISH LIKE THIS,
BUT I'M STARVING.
AND I THINK, OUT OF
ALL THE FISH THAT I'VE CAUGHT,
I DESERVE THIS ONE.
AND I'M NOT GONNA TAKE HIM BACK
TO CAMP AND ARGUE WITH ANYBODY.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAT ME OUT
ON THE LAST CHALLENGE,
AND THEY LOST THE FOOD REWARD.
WELL, THAT'S MY FOOD REWARD.
(\LAUGHS\)
FOR ALL MY HARD WORK.
THIS IS THE FIRST THING
I'VE DONE BEHIND ANYBODY'S BACK,
OTHER THAN VOTE FOR MARTY.
(\LAUGHS\)
BUT I'M GOING TO DIG INTO
THIS THING RIGHT NOW AND SEE...
IF IT IS DONE,
AND I DON'T CARE IF IT'S BLACK.
BON APPETIT!
(\LAUGHS\)
(\COW MOOS\)
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> OH, GOSH!
>> UNBELIEVABLE!
>> WHEN I SAW THE FOOD THAT
WAS PREPARED ON THE TABLE...
THIS IS WHAT
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
...NOT EATING FOR 16 DAYS
AND SEEING FOOD,
I ACTUALLY STARTED TO SHAKE.
WATERMELON, I JUST LOVE IT.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
>> ALINA AND CHASE, YOU'VE
BOTH CALLED OUR CAMP HOME.
>> HAVE WE?
>> UH-HUH.
>> IT'S HOME.
>> WE TAKE FOR GRANTED SITTING
DOWN AND HAVING A MEAL TOGETHER.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR HOW MANY DAYS,
AND THE SIX OF US SITTING DOWN
AND BEING SO APPRECIATIVE
OF A MEAL, IT WAS...
IT BECAME VERY EMOTIONAL
FOR A LOT OF US.
>> (\CRYING\): INCREDIBLE.
AFTER 17 DAYS OF NOT EATING
AND NOT BEING WITH FAMILY
OR ANYTHING, I MEAN...
>> WE'RE KICKING ASS, Y'ALL.
WE'RE DOING THIS, MAN,
WE'RE DOING THIS.
>> OH, GOD...
>> ALINA'S SO GRIMY,
SHE'S SO GRIMY AND SO SNEAKY.
I THINK SHE GOT EMOTIONAL
BECAUSE SHE'S TRYING
TO KEEP HERSELF IN THE GAME.
BUT I CAN PUT ON A SHOW,
JUST LIKE ALINA.
I HAVE BEEN PLAYING A ROLE.
WE HAVE BEEN GETTING CLOSE,
YOU KNOW?
THIS IS ALL A PART OF MY PLAN.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE WALKING AWAY
AND YOUR TORCH IS PUT OUT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, FIRST THINGS FIRST.
I WILL TAKE BACK THE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY NECKLACES.
THANK YOU.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY NO MORE.
ONCE AGAIN TRIBAL IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
LET'S GET TO TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
STANDING AT THE TOP OF A TOWER,
TWO MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE
WILL ROLL CANNON BALLS
DOWN A LONG, STEEP CHUTE
WHILE FOUR OTHER MEMBERS
WILL USE ROPES
IN AN ATTEMPT TO AIM THE CHUTE,
TRYING TO BREAK
ONE OF THE OTHER TRIBE'S TILES.
FIRST TRIBE TO BREAK ALL FIVE
OF THE OTHER TRIBE'S TILES
WINS IMMUNITY
AND IS SAFE IN THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE THE EIGHTH PERSON
WILL BE VOTED OUT OF THE GAME.
LA FLOR, YOU HAVE
ONE EXTRA PERSON.
CANNOT SIT OUT THE SAME PERSON
IN BACK-TO-BACK CHALLENGES.
JANE SAT OUT THE LAST CHALLENGE.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> I'M GOING TO SIT OUT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: SASH GONNA SIT OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE,
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO STRATEGIZE,
AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
UP TOP FOR ESPADA:
BENRY AND ALINA.
ON THE ROPES FOR ESPADA:
CHASE, HOLLY, NAONKA AND DAN.
UP TOP FOR LA FLOR:
BRENDA AND PURPLE KELLY.
ON THE ROPES:
JILL, MARTY, JANE, FABIO.
HERE WE GO.
>> ALL RIGHT, PULL IT UP.
WATCH OUT.
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
>> LOWER IT DOWN,
LOWER IT DOWN.
>> CHASE AND HOLLY,
A LITTLE LOWER.
>> Jeff: TAKES SOME WORK
TO MOVE THESE ROPES AROUND.
>> MARTY AND JILL, UP, PLEASE.
EVERYONE... OKAY, STOP.
OKAY, NAY AND DAN,
PULL A LITTLE MORE.
>> TOO MUCH.
>> RIGHT THERE, RIGHT THERE.
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: THERE ARE THREE LEVELS
YOU CAN SHOOT FROM
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> DO THIS ONE.
>> Jeff: ESPADA HAS IT LINED UP.
WHERE'S BENRY GOING
TO DROP THE BALL?
HE'S MOVING DOWN.
BENRY WITH ONE
OF THOSE SMALL CANNONBALLS.
THERE ARE TWO SIZES.
BALL IS EN ROUTE.
JUST SHORT.
KELLY LETS IT GO.
AND IT CONNECTS!
LA FLOR TAKES
AN EARLY LEAD ONE-ZIP.
>> NAY, LIKE, UH, TOOT!
BOOM.
>> JILL AND MARTY,
PULL MORE, PLEASE.
PULL MORE.
>> THAT LOOKS SUPER GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT, I THINK
A BIG ONE MIGHT HIT THAT.
>> Jeff: ALINA READY
WITH ESPADA'S SECOND SHOT.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: AND IT CONNECTS!
JUST MISSES.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: WE ARE TIED ONE-ONE.
>> NAONKA AND DAN,
GIVE A NICE LITTLE PULL.
A NICE ONE.
LET'S GO FOR THAT OTHER BIG BOY.
>> MARTY AND JILL, PULL.
KEEP PULLING.
OKAY, STOP.
>> IT'S, LIKE,
TWO FEET LOWER THAN IT WAS.
>> IT'S TWO FEET LOWER
THAN THAT LAST SHOT.
I THINK WE SHOULD GO UP
A LITTLE BIT.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, I THINK
THAT MIGHT BE PERFECT.
>> Jeff: ESPADA READY.
BENRY LETS IT LOOSE.
AND HE CONNECTS!
>> WHOO!
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY
LETS IT FLY.
JUST MISSES.
ESPADA LEADS TWO-ONE.
>> YOU GUYS, I KNEW IT.
>> IT HAS TO BE LOWER.
>> CHASE AND HOLLY,
DROP A LITTLE.
>> DROP.
>> OH! YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> ARE YOU MAKING IT LOWER?
>> YEAH, IT'S, LIKE,
SIX INCHES, EIGHT INCHES.
>> DO IT MORE.
>> GO DOWN THE LEVEL
WITH THE BIG BALL. TRUST ME.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD
PULL UP A LITTLE BIT.
>> FABIO, COME ON,
LAST TIME I LISTENED TO YOU.
>> Jeff: ALINA READY FOR ESPADA.
SHE'S MOVED DOWN
TO THE SECOND LEVEL.
>> DROP.
>> Jeff:
GOING FOR A CLOSER TARGET.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: AND SHE CONNECTS!
>> LET'S GO, BRENDA!
>> Jeff: BRENDA HOPING
TO SCORE FOR LA FLOR.
JUST MISSES.
ESPADA NOW LEADS THREE-ONE.
>> WE NEED TO GO BACK
TO THAT FIRST ONE WE TRIED,
BECAUSE WE SEE
WHERE THE FIRST ONE HIT.
>> WE GOT LITTLE BALLS.
>> I KNOW. I KNOW, BUT...
>> ARE WE GOOD?
WILL YOU TELL US?
>> IT WAS RIGHT ON,
IT WAS JUST TOO SHORT,
SO WE'RE GOING TO GET
MORE MOMENTUM UP HERE.
>> Jeff: BENRY MOVING DOWN
TO THE SECOND LEVEL
FOR ESPADA'S NEXT SHOT.
>> COME ON, BENRY!
>> COME ON, BEN!
>> Jeff: BENRY RELEASES.
>> OH, BABY! WHOO-HOO-HOO!
>> Jeff: AND IT CONNECTS!
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> LET'S GO, GUYS.
>> Jeff:
BRENDA READY FOR LA FLOR.
SHE RELEASES.
AND JUST MISSES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: ESPADA
NOW LEADS FOUR-ONE.
THERE ARE FIVE TILES TO BREAK.
>> I NEED NAY AND DAN TO PULL.
>> PULL UP. RIGHT THERE.
>> YOU GUYS HAVE GOT
TO BOTH TALK ABOUT IT UP THERE.
>> WE ARE. WE'RE BOTH
TALKING ABOUT IT UP HERE.
>> FEELING THAT, BABY.
>> YEAH?
>> YEP LET IT GO.
>> Jeff: ESPADA
COULD WIN IT WITH THIS.
>> OH! JUST BARELY. DON'T MOVE.
>> Jeff: JUST SHORT.
LA FLOR STILL ALIVE.
LA FLOR NEEDS TO SCORE HERE,
TRAILING FOUR-ONE.
>> I'M GOING TO LET IT GO.
>> Jeff: DOWN ON THE THIRD LEVEL
WITH THE BIGGER BALL.
AND IT WORKED--
LA FLOR SCORES!
LA FLOR NOW HAS TWO,
ESPADA AT FOUR.
>> YOU WANT TO GO
WITH THE BIG ONE?
>> LET'S TRY A BIG ONE.
>> GO GRAB A BIG ONE.
>> HOW DOES IT LOOK FROM THERE
IF I LAUNCH A BIG ONE FROM HERE?
DOES IT LOOK GOOD?
>> Jeff:
ESPADA GOING TO CHANGE BALLS,
GOING WITH
THE BIGGER CANNONBALL.
A LOT OF STRATEGY.
>> THE AIM IS PERFECT, GUYS,
BUT WE'RE OVERSHOOTING.
>> WHEN I WENT DOWN THERE,
THOUGH, IT WAS SUPER SHORT.
>> IT'S GETTING HARD DOWN HERE.
>> Jeff: ESPADA COULD WIN IT
WITH THIS TOSS.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: AND THEY DO!
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> Jeff: ESPADA WINS IMMUNITY!
>> I SHOULD BE A PIRATE!
>> YES!
>> I REALLY FELT
LIKE WE HAD THAT.
>> ME, TOO.
>> Jeff:
ESPADA, CONGRATULATIONS.
BACK-TO-BACK WINS, ALINA.
GOT TO FEEL GOOD.
>> IT FEELS ABSOLUTELY AMAZING.
>> Jeff: NOBODY GOING HOME
FROM ESPADA.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
>> Jeff: LA FLOR,
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
THE EIGHTH PERSON
WILL BE VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO THAT'S GOING TO BE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> LOSING IMMUNITY TODAY,
FOR ME, MEANS THAT WE GO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND THE WAY
THINGS ARE SHAPING UP,
IT LOOKS LIKE
THE REMAINING LA FLOR MEMBERS
WANT MARTY OR I GONE, AND BEING
THAT HE HAS THE IMMUNITY IDOL,
IT WILL PROBABLY BE ME.
>> FABIO.
>> FABS.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO GO TONIGHT?
>> WE GOT TO SPLIT...
WE GOT TO PUT THREE ON MARTY,
TWO ON JILL,
MAKE MARTY PLAY THE IDOL, JILL
AND WHOEVER THEY VOTE FOR TIE...
>> WHICH WOULD MEAN A TIE.
>> AND THEN
WE'LL ALL VOTE JILL OUT.
>> OKAY, JANE NEEDS
HER SATISFACTION
OF VOTING FOR MARTY, I THINK.
>> JANE, ARE YOU GOING
TO VOTE FOR MARTY?
>> I'M SORRY, I WAS
THE UGLY DUCKLING OVER THERE.
>> YOU'RE A PRIZED POSSESSION
OVER HERE.
>> I'M A FIRM BELIEVER,
WHAT GOES AROUND COMES AROUND.
MARTY AND JILL HAVE TREATED ME
LIKE I DON'T EXIST FROM DAY ONE,
GOING ALL THE WAY BACK
TO THE ESPADA TRIBE.
I MEAN, I REALLY FELT LIKE
THE UGLY DUCKLING OVER THERE,
AND I KNOW I GAINED
THE RESPECT OF BRENDA,
PURPLE KELLY, FABIO AND SASH.
SO AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I HOPE MARTY GOES HOME.
IT'S STILL ICING ON THE CAKE
IF JILL GOES HOME. (\LAUGHS\)
I WANT THE CAKE,
AND I WANT TO EAT IT, TOO,
AND I WANT BOTH OF THEM GONE.
(\LAUGHS\)
>> WHY DON'T I DO THIS?
WHY DON'T I GO UP TO MARTY
AND TELL HIM IT'S GOING TO BE
THREE VOTES FOR YOU,
TWO VOTES FOR JILL,
WHICH MEANS YOU HAVE
TO PLAY YOUR IDOL TONIGHT,
OR... I GUARANTEE YOU...
>> YOU WON'T GO HOME.
>> ...JILL WILL GO HOME,
AND GIVE ME THE IDOL
SO THAT WE HAVE IT
>> RIGHT NOW THE GAME PLAN IS,
PUT THREE OF OUR VOTES ON MARTY
AND TWO ON JILL,
AND TELL MARTY, LIKE, "BRO,
YOU GOTTA PLAY THE IDOL NOW,"
SO HE DOES,
AND THEN IT WILL BE A TIE
BETWEEN JILL AND WHOEVER
MARTY... AND JILL VOTE.
AND THEN ON THE REVOTE,
JILL WOULD END UP GOING HOME.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I THINK WE SHOULD
REALLY CONSIDER THIS.
ASK MARTY FOR THE IDOL.
TELL HIM, "YOU'RE SAFE,
GIVE US THE IDOL,
WE'LL VOTE OUT JILL,"
AND THEN WE VOTE HIM OUT.
>> THE... THEN THE ONLY PROBLEM
I SEE WITH THAT IS THAT JILL
WILL HAVE
ABSOLUTELY NO ALLEGIANCE
OR CONFIDENCE IN US.
>> IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
EITHER WAY.
YOU THINK SHE WILL EVER,
EVER, EVER TRUST US?
WE JUST VOTED OUT MARTY.
>> TH-THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
>> OR-OR WE VOTE OUT HER.
EITHER ONE, THEY DON'T TRUST US,
AND THEY NEVER WILL TRUST US.
THEY'RE NOT THAT DUMB, SASH.
TONIGHT EITHER MARTY OR JILL
IS GOING TO GO HOME.
THAT'S THE PLAN.
SASH AND I ARE BOTH STUCK
ON WHAT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO,
AND WE'RE WONDERING,
WHAT IF WE COULD BE,
LIKE, SUPER MEAN, ASK MARTY FOR
THE IDOL AND VOTE HIS ASS OUT.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
SUCH A TOUGH DAY, DUDE.
SO... WHAT THEY'RE SAYING IS...
THEY'LL SPLIT THE VOTE
THREE TO TWO TONIGHT.
>> THREE VOTES FOR YOU;
>> YEAH.
>> TWO VOTES FOR JILL,
>> IN HOPES THAT-THE
THE IDOL IS FLUSHED,
>> YEAH.
>> UM, AND THEN IT'D GO TO A TIE
AND THEN IN A TIEBREAKER,
JILL WOULD GO HOME.
>> YEAH.
>> UM, THE OTHER OPTION
TO STRENGTHEN US...
YOU HAND THE IDOL OVER
AND I LOOK YOU IN THE EYE,
MAN TO MAN,
AND SHAKE YOUR HAND
THAT YOU'RE
NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> RIGHT.
YEAH, BUT I...
>> WOULD YOU DO THAT?
>> I'D JUST GO HOME NEXT TIME.
>> LOOK, IF THIS HAPPENS,
IF YOU GIVE IT TO ME,
UM, I'LL LOOK YOU IN THE EYE
AND SHAKE YOUR HAND AGAIN.
IF WE LOSE
THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
I'M GONNA
GIVE YOU BACK THE IDOL.
YOU KNOW, JILL'S
GOING HOME, REGARDLESS.
>> I CAN'T VOTE FOR HER.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> I HOPE YOUR PEOPLE
UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> NO, NO, NO. YOU...
YOU'LL VOTE FOR...
>> JANE.
>> JANE, BRENDA,
WHOEVER YOU WANT.
I THINK IT MAKES SENSE,
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S...
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T TELL YOU WHAT
TO DO WITH YOUR OWN IDOL, SO...
>> RIGHT NOW I FEEL...
ABSOLUTELY POWERLESS IN EVERY...
WAY, SHAPE OR FORM.
IF I KEEP THE IDOL...
I HAVE TO USE THE IDOL
TONIGHT, SO...
I GIVE SASH THE IDOL,
AND MAYBE I GO HOME TONIGHT,
MAYBE I DON'T.
I GOT TO GIVE THE IDOL
TO SOMEBODY,
SO I'M EITHER GIVING IT
TO JEFF TONIGHT
OR I'M GIVING IT TO SASH.
A CURSE AT TIMES,
A GOOD THING AT TIMES--
THE IMMUNITY IDOL IS YOURS.
>> THANK YOU, BROTHER.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER, OKAY?
>> IT'S IN YOUR HANDS.
I'D RATHER GIVE IT TO SASH,
BECAUSE MAYBE,
IF HE LIVES UP TO HIS WORD,
I WOULD MAYBE LIVE
ONE MORE CYCLE.
ONE MORE CYCLE
COULD POTENTIALLY GET ME
TO THE MERGE,
AND THEN THINGS ARE WIDE OPEN.
>> WELL, IT TURNS OUT I DON'T
EVEN HAVE TO DIG FOR IDOLS.
ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS ASK FOR THEM.
PEOPLE WILL LITERALLY
HAND ME AN IDOL
JUST BECAUSE I MAY OR MAY NOT
KEEP THEM IN THE GAME
A LITTLE LONGER.
MARTY MADE A BIG MISTAKE.
THAT'S PROBABLY HIS BIGGEST
MISTAKE IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: SO FABIO, BACK-TO-BACK
LOSSES, REWARD AND IMMUNITY.
DOES ESPADA HAVE MOMENTUM?
>> YEAH.
I THINK THEIR SPIRITS ARE UP.
I THINK THEY HAVE MOMENTUM.
I THINK THEY'RE A STRONG TRIBE.
I THINK WE'RE ALSO STRONG.
I THINK TOMORROW OR THE NEXT
REWARD CHALLENGE,
I THINK IT WILL STILL BE AN EVEN
PLAYING FIELD.
BUT, YEAH, THEY'RE FEELING GOOD
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: JANE, LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL WAS CRAZY.
PEOPLE BEING SURPRISED,
DOUBLE CROSSES.
WHAT WAS THE VIBE BEFORE
THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL?
>> SOME OF US GOT TOGETHER
AND TALKED;
THE ONES OF US THAT HAVE MESHED
TOGETHER REALLY GOOD,
AND WE MADE A DECISION.
>> Jeff: IS IT OBVIOUS, JANE,
WHO DOESN'T MESH TOGETHER?
WHO'S ON THE OUTSIDE?
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: AND DO THEY KNOW
THEY'RE ON THE OUTSIDE?
>> I THINK SO. MM-HMM.
>> Jeff: MARTY,
DO YOU FEEL THAT?
THERE'S A SENSE OF BEING IN
WITH THE GROUP
AND BEING OUTSIDE OF THE GROUP?
>> YEAH, CLEARLY.
I MEAN, WE CAME IN AS A MINORITY
INTO THIS TRIBE,
AND SOME OF US DID MORE
OF A FLIP-FLOP,
AND SOME OF US JUST TRIED
TO INCORPORATE OURSELVES
WHERE WE FELT WE FIT IN.
>> Jeff: WHO FLIP-FLOPPED?
>> I THINK JANE'S A FLIPPER.
SHE'LL GO WHEREVER THE WIND
BLOWS IN TERMS OF MAKING SURE
THAT SHE SAVES HER OWN SKIN,
AND WE TRIED TO REMAIN STRONG
AND TRIED TO FIT IN
WITH WHOEVER WE COULD.
>> Jeff: "WE" MEANING YOU
AND JILL.
>> JILL AND I, YEAH.
>> Jeff: JANE, FAIR CRITICISM?
>> WELL, WHEN WE BECAME YELLOW,
I BECAME YELLOW.
AND THAT'S THE WAY I LOOK AT IT.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, COULD YOU FEEL
THAT FROM JANE?
>> TOTALLY.
FROM DAY ONE.
SHE JUST...
SHE'S JUST VERY GENUINE.
SHE NEVER REALLY TRIED TO MAKE
AN ALLIANCE,
IT JUST BECAME
A NATURAL FRIENDSHIP.
>> Jeff: JILL, DO YOU FEEL
THE SEPARATION?
>> OH, DEFINITELY.
FROM THE MINUTE WE GOT TO CAMP,
CLEARLY IT'S AN OLD/YOUNG
DIVISION THAT STILL EXISTS.
SO IT'S A LITTLE FRUSTRATING
TO BE PUT IN THAT SITUATION,
BUT IT'S MY OBLIGATION TO PLAY
OUT OF IT IF I CAN.
>> Jeff: MARTY, LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL
THERE WAS A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT THE IDOL,
AND THE FACT THAT YOU HAD IT,
WOULD YOU PLAY IT OR NOT.
DID THAT COME UP AGAIN TODAY?
>> OH, SURE. AND YOU COULD ARGUE
THAT MAYBE IT WAS THE STUPIDEST
MOVE NOT TO PLAY IT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL
OR YOU COULD ARGUE THAT IT WAS
THE GUTSIEST MOVE.
BUT I WENT WITH MY GUT INSTINCTS
AND DECIDED TO HOLD ONTO IT.
BUT TONIGHT, YOU KNOW, IS THE
FIRST TIME THAT I FEEL LIKE
I MAY HAVE MADE A MISTAKE
THIS EVENING.
I'M AT A DISADVANTAGE NOW.
AND SO DO YOU DO SOMETHING,
TRUST SOMEBODY AND TRANSFER
THE POWER OF THE IDOL, AND MAYBE
IF THINGS WORK OUT AND YOU TAKE
A RISK, IT BUYS YOU A LITTLE
MORE TIME IN THIS GAME, WHICH,
IT'S A CRAZY GAME, YOU NEVER
KNOW WHAT CAN HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, WORRIED ABOUT
WHERE THE IDOL IS?
DO YOU KNOW WHERE THE IDOL IS?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW PHYSICALLY
WHERE IT IS.
I THINK SASH HAS IT.
>> JEFF, THE IDOL IS IN
MY POCKET.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS IN HIS POCKET.
>> Jeff: SO MARTY, WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THE IDOL?
>> IN TALKING TO SASH, WE AGREED
THAT I WOULD TRANSFER THE IDOL
TO HIM.
>> Jeff: SO YOU GAVE YOUR IDOL
TO SASH?
>> I DID. IT COULD GO DOWN
AS ONE OF THE STUPIDEST MOVES
EVER OR MAYBE NOT.
>> Jeff: FABIO, REASONABLE OF
MARTY TO BE A LITTLE CONCERNED
THAT HE MIGHT HAVE
JUST MADE A BLUNDER?
>> YEAH, I THINK IT'S VERY
REASONABLE
BECAUSE WE COULD EASILY VOTE HIM
OUT TONIGHT.
BUT EITHER WAY,
WE HAVE THE IDOL, SO I THINK
WE COME OUT ON TOP.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, IT'S
INTERESTING THAT FABIO SAYS,
"WE HAVE THE IDOL."
>> I THINK IT'S OKAY TO SAY "WE"
BECAUSE THAT IS HOW MUCH
WE TRUST SASH.
>> Jeff: SASH, OF COURSE YOU
THINK THIS MAKES PERFECT SENSE
'CAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH IT IN YOUR POCKET.
JUST OUT OF CURIOUSITY,
NOW THAT YOU HAVE IT IN
YOUR POSSESSION FOR THE GROUP,
YOU WANT TO GIVE IT TO BRENDA
TO HOLD ONTO?
>> IF THAT'S WHAT WE DECIDE
AS A GROUP,
THEN MAYBE BACK AT CAMP
I MIGHT DO THAT.
AT THIS MOMENT I DON'T THINK
IT SERVES A PURPOSE.
BUT IF THERE'S A TIME
WHEN I LOSE TRUST IN THEM...
I'M SORRY.
IF THERE'S A TIME WHEN THEY LOSE
TRUST IN ME,
THEN I'LL HAVE TO TURN IT OVER
OR I'LL HAVE THE BIGGEST TARGET
ON MY BACK OF THIS ENTIRE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: GOTTA ASK, SASH, YOU
SAID IT, I JUST HEARD IT.
FREUDIAN SLIP?
IF THERE COMES A TIME WHEN YOU
LOSE TRUST IN THEM
AND YOU HAVE THAT IDOL
IN YOUR POCKET?
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT TO
SAY, BUT THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
>> Jeff: FABIO, ARE YOU FAMILIAR
WITH THE PSYCHOLOGIST FREUD?
>> YES, I'M ACTUALLY A LITTLE
BIT FAMILIAR
WITH FREUDIAN PSYCHOLOGY.
IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN THE WHOLE 90%
OF THE SUBCONSCIOUS
OMING UP ABOVE AND COMING OUT.
>> Jeff: BRENDA,
THAT'S GONNA LINGER
IN YOUR BRAIN FOR A WHILE.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, IT WAS A SLIP.
>> Jeff: JANE, HOW BIG A MISTAKE
COULD IT BE FOR MARTY TO GIVE UP
THAT IDOL TO SASH
BEFORE TRIBAL COUNCIL?
>> WELL, ANY TIME YOU WATCH THIS
GAME AND YOU GIVE UP THE IDOL,
IT COMES BACK TO HAUNT YOU.
>> Jeff: OKAY, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
JANE, YOU'RE UP.
>> THIS GAME AIN'T OVER YET.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT. ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JANE.
JANE. TWO VOTES JANE.
JILL.
TWO VOTES JANE, ONE VOTE JILL.
MARTY.
TWO VOTES JANE, ONE VOTE JILL,
ONE VOTE MARTY.
JILL.
THAT'S TWO VOTES JANE, TWO VOTES
JILL, ONE VOTE MARTY.
MARTY.
WE'RE TIED.
JANE HAS TWO VOTES, JILL HAS TWO
VOTES, MARTY HAS TWO VOTES.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA...
JILL.
>> Jeff: JILL,
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT'S CLEAR FROM
THE VOTE THAT THIS GROUP IS
MAKING DECISIONS
BASED ON LOYALTY.
THE QUESTION IS HOW LONG CAN
THAT LOYALTY LAST?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR:
>> UNCLE FABIO FOUND
SOME TREEMAIL!
>> Jeff: THE MERGE BRINGS
EVERYONE TOGETHER.
>> IF THAT CHEST IS ALONE,
I'M TAKING SOME STUFF OUT OF IT.
>> Jeff: SO NAONKA WORKS
OVERTIME TO TEAR EVERYONE APART.
>> THAT WAS PRETTY FRUSTRATING
WHEN WE REALIZED
ALL THESE THINGS WERE MISSING.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE!
>> UM, REALLY GRATEFUL FOR THE
OPPORTUNITY THAT I'VE HAD
TO MEET A LOT
OF FANTASTIC PEOPLE.
MARTY, COULD LUCK TO YOU.
MY KIDS NEED SOMEONE
TO ROOT FOR NOW,
SO I HOPE YOU GO
ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
AND I JUST WANT TO SAY
HOW MUCH THIS HAS MADE ME
APPRECIATE MY HUSBAND
AND MY CHILDREN.
AND I HOPE
THAT THEY'RE PROUD OF ME
FOR WHAT I'VE DONE HERE.