>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR:
SASH AND BRENDA WERE KING
AND QUEEN OF THE BEACH.
>> WE'RE THE TWO MOST POWERFUL
PEOPLE IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: AND THEY THOUGHT
EVERYONE ELSE WAS A PEASANT.
>> PEOPLE NEED TO REMEMBER
WHERE THEIR PLACE IS.
>> Jeff: THEIR ALLIANCE WAS
STRENGTHENED
BY TWO HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS.
BRENDA'S BEST FRIEND
NAONKA HAD ONE...
>> IT'S THE KEY TO OUR LIFE
IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: ...AND SASH HAD
THE OTHER.
BUT SOME OF THE PEASANTS
WERE GETTING RESTLESS.
>> THERE IS A TEMPTATION
TO WANT TO SUDDENLY JUST TAKE
CONTROL AND MAKE A MOVE.
WHOO!
>> YEAH, MARTY!
>> Jeff: SO AT THE REWARD FEAST,
MARTY SUCCUMBED TO TEMPTATION
AND TRIED TO LAUNCH
AN ALL-GUYS REBELLION.
>> WE'RE TAKING THIS THING
TO THE END, MEN.
>> WE EARNED IT!
>> NICE JOB TODAY, MAN.
>> Jeff: FABIO AND BENRY
IMMEDIATELY JUMPED ON BOARD.
>> MARTY'S A SMART GUY.
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
>> Jeff: SASH FOOLED MARTY
BY PRETENDING
TO JOIN UP WITH HIM.
>> I TRIED TO BOOST HIS EGO
SO THAT HE'LL CONTINUE
TO COME BACK TO ME.
>> Jeff: MARTY DIDN'T APPROACH
CHASE BECAUSE HE WAS TOO CLOSE
WITH BRENDA AND JANE.
>> I WANTED TO SHOW THE GIRLS
THEY CAN TRUST ME,
AND HOPEFULLY THAT WILL GET ME
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
BRENDA AND SASH SQUASHED
MARTY'S PLAN...
MARTY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
...AND MARTY ALONG WITH HIM.
NOW BRENDA AND SASH HAVE
SO MUCH POWER
THAT EVERYONE IS LOOKING
OVER THEIR SHOULDER.
TEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL REALLY SHOWED
WHERE THE ALLEGIANCE REALLY IS.
BENRY, FABIO, AND DAN NOW SEE
THAT SASH AND I
AREN'T ON THEIR SIDE.
AND WE TOOK OUT
THEIR LITTLE LEADER MARTY.
AND NOW IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME BEFORE THEY GO.
I'M GONNA GET A GOOD NIGHT'S
SLEEP TONIGHT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I THINK SASH AND I BEING
IN CONTROL
DOES LOOK LIKE A KING-
AND-QUEEN SITUATION.
BUT SASH IS MORE OF A QUEEN
AND I'M MORE OF A KING
IS THE WAY I LOOK AT IT.
>> I KNOW.
>> JANE AND I BOTH HAD
THE SAME FEELING:
BRENDA IS BASICALLY CALLING
ALL THE SHOTS.
SO WE ARE TOTALLY GONNA MAKE A
POWER MOVE BEFORE NEXT TRIBAL.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY,
WHAT DO I HAVE TO LOSE?
SOMETHING HAS TO CHANGE,
AND IT HAS TO CHANGE SOON.
♪ ♪
>> THIS RAIN IS BAD, MAN.
THE ELEMENTS OUT HERE
CAN REALLY GET YOU.
THIS MORNING, WE WOKE UP, AND IT
LOOKED LIKE IT WAS GONNA RAIN.
WE ALL KNOW THAT IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT THE FIRE
AT LEAST STAYS GOING.
SO WE MOVED, LIKE, ALL OF THE
CHESTS AROUND THE FIRE
TO PROTECT IT FROM THE RAIN.
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
>> I GOT UP THREE TIMES IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
AND I WAS GONNA WAKE YOU UP,
AND THEN I DIDN'T.
>> I'VE COME A LONG WAY
IN THIS GAME.
DAY FIVE, I WAS READY TO LEAVE,
AND HERE I AM, SITTING HERE
WITH 14 DAYS LEFT.
I'M, LIKE, "MY GOSH.
I COULD REALLY KEEP GOING."
SO RIGHT NOW, JANE AND I, WE'RE
TRYING TO RALLY A VOTE
AGAINST BRENDA OR SASH.
>> WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?
>> SASH AND BRENDA TOLD YOU GUYS
THEY WERE VOTING FOR JANE.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND THEY SWITCHED,
AND THEY VOTED FOR MARTY.
THEY ARE IN TOTAL CONTROL.
>> SASH JUST BACKSTABBED HIM
LAST NIGHT.
>> TERRIBLY!
>> TERRIBLY.
>> SO HOW CAN YOU TRUST BRENDA
AND SASH
WHEN WHAT THEY DID
AT TRIBAL LAST NIGHT?
>> I CAN'T.
>> EVERYBODY'S LISTENING
TO BRENDA, INCLUDING ME.
KELLY PURPLE CRAWLS UP
BRENDA'S ...
SHE DOES EXACTLY
WHAT SHE WANTS TO DO.
BRENDA IS ALSO ANOTHER THREAT
BECAUSE SHE'S REALLY GOOD
AT CHALLENGES.
AND SHE'S GONNA TAKE YOU GUYS
OUT ONE BY ONE.
>> HOLLY ABSOLUTELY GAVE ME
A LITTLE BIT OF A WAKE-UP CALL
THIS MORNING.
SHE'S GOT A GREAT PLAN,
ACTUALLY.
AND I'M ALL FOR IT, YOU KNOW?
GETTING RID OF SASH AND BRENDA
IS NUMBER ONE
ON MY LIST RIGHT NOW.
>> BRENDA'S THE QUEEN BEE
AND KNOWS THIS GAME IN AND OUT.
SHE MUST HAVE BEEN STUDYING
THIS FOREVER.
>> BRENDA IS PLAYING THIS GAME
SO WELL
TO WHERE SHE'S OVER-THINKING.
SHE'S MARTY, JR.
SHE'S BECOME A VILLAIN.
SHE BEFRIENDS YOU, AND THEN SHE
THROWS YOU TO THE WOLVES.
>> BRENDA, SHE'S LIKE MY BEST
FRIEND OUT HERE,
BUT DID I COME OUT HERE ALL THIS
WAY FROM SOUTH CENTRAL L.A.
TO GO BACK HOME WITH NOTHING?
NO. THIS IS A GAME.
AND BRENDA IS A THREAT.
SO RIGHT NOW, WHILE WE HAVE
EVERYBODY AGAINST HER,
NOW IS THE TIME TO GET HER OUT.
>> WE NEED TO SEE WHO WINS
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
AND THEN WE NEED TO DECIDE.
BUT I THINK
WE'RE ALL IN A CONSENSUS
THAT BRENDA HAS TO GO FIRST.
SHE'S THE RINGLEADER.
>> THINGS ARE GETTING A LITTLE
CRAZY HERE AT CAMP.
THERE'S TWO ALLIANCES NOW,
AND I PERSONALLY THINK IT COULD
BE THE BEST INTEREST
TO VOTE BENRY OUT FIRST.
I STILL DON'T TRUST BENRY.
BENRY'S ON HIS LAST ROPE.
HE SCREWED UP
WHEN HE VOTED WITH MARTY,
PLUS HE'S A BIG PHYSICAL THREAT.
AND AS OF RIGHT NOW,
I DON'T THINK BRENDA AND SASH
HAVE LIED TO ME.
SO I'M STUCK IN THE MIDDLE OF
TWO ALLIANCES AGAIN.
>> CHASE, YOU'VE GOT
TO BELIEVE ME ON THIS ONE.
SHE IS TOTALLY RUNNING THE SHOW.
>> I THINK YOU'RE WRONG.
CHASE WAS A LITTLE LEERY
ABOUT THE PLAN.
HE WAS A LITTLE CONCERNED
ABOUT BEN.
SO I'M KEEPING MY EYE ON CHASE
JUST BECAUSE CHASE,
I FEEL I CAN TRUST HIM,
BUT AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME,
HE MAKES ME
JUST A LITTLE NERVOUS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> ALL: YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU WILL BE DIVIDED
INTO TWO TEAMS OF FIVE.
USING ONLY FOUR BARRELS, TWO
PLANKS, AND TEN FEET OF ROPE,
YOU MUST WORK TOGETHER TO MAKE
YOUR WAY ACROSS THE BEACH
TO THE FINISHED PLATFORM
WITHOUT TOUCHING THE GROUND.
IF ANYBODY FROM YOUR TEAM
TOUCHES THE GROUND,
THE ENTIRE TEAM HAS
TO GO BACK TO THE START.
FIRST TEAM TO GET
ALL FIVE MEMBERS
TO THE FINISH PLATFORM
WIN REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> ALL: YES!
>> Reporter: THE WINNING TEAM
WILL TRAVEL TO THE CERRO NEGRO,
ONE OF THE MOST ACTIVE VOLCANOES
IN THE WORLD.
YOU'LL DO A LITTLE VOLCANO
BOARDING,
AND THEN YOU'LL AND ENJOY PIZZA,
SOFT DRINKS, CHOCOLATE BROWNIES.
(ALL GROAN)
>> OH, MY GOD, BABY.
>> Jeff: I KNOW IT'S WORTH
PLAYING FOR.
WE'LL DO A SCHOOLYARD PICK
TO GET OUR TEAMS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ON THE BLUE TEAM: CHASE, PURPLE
KELLY, JANE, NAONKA, AND FABIO.
ON THE YELLOW TEAM: SASH, HOLLY,
BRENDA, DAN, AND BENRY.
FOR REWARD. SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU HAVE FOUR BARRELS,
TWO PLANKS OF WOOD,
AND TEN FEET OF ROPE.
WHAT YOU DO WITH IT
WILL DETERMINE
WHO WINS THIS CHALLENGE.
BOTH TEAMS OFF TO A GOOD START
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT A SYSTEM,
WHAT'S GONNA BE THE KEY
TO MOVING THE ENTIRE TEAM
OF FIVE ACROSS THE BEACH WHEN
YOU CAN'T TOUCH THE GROUND?
>> STAY LOW, CHASE, STAY LOW.
STAY LOW.
>> KEEP IT CLOSE!
KEEP IT CLOSE!
>> ROLL THAT TO SASH.
>> PURPLE KELLY, CAN YOU REACH
THAT BARREL?
>> SEE IF YOU CAN GET YOUR FEET
BEHIND YOU.
>> WHERE DO YOU WANT ME?
>> Jeff: BLUE TEAM WANTS
THEIR LAST BARREL
AND CAN'T GET IT.
>> I DON'T THINK WE NEED IT.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> LET'S GO WITH IT.
>> Jeff: DAN, BATTLING
TWO BAD KNEES,
GONNA TRY TO GET UP
ON THIS BARREL.
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IT'S
COMFORTABLE, BUT HE'S UP THERE.
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
BLUE TEAM HAS A SYSTEM
AND IT IS WORKING,
ONLY USING THREE
OF THEIR FOUR BARRELS.
YELLOW TEAM JUST WINGING IT.
A LITTLE CIRQUE DE SOLEIL GOING
ON WITH BENRY.
CHASE HAS A VERY GOOD STRATEGY
FOR THE BLUE TEAM.
>> LET'S DO WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
WE'RE GONNA LOSE
THAT FOURTH BARREL.
>> Jeff: BLUE TEAM WORKING
TOGETHER, VERY CALM.
YELLOW TEAM LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE IN PAIN,
CRUNCHED OVER, CONFUSED.
>> IT'S ROLLING! IT'S ROLLING!
>> Jeff: YELLOW TEAM,
EVERYBODY FALLS OFF.
EVERYBODY BACK TO THE START.
DAN IS HURT.
DAN SMASHED HIS HAND.
HUGE SETBACK
FOR THE YELLOW TEAM.
THE ONLY THING THE YELLOW TEAM
CAN HOPE FOR
IS A MISTAKE BY THE BLUE TEAM.
BRENDA TRYING TO ROLL
ON ONE OF THE BARRELS.
THAT'LL WORK, FOR A MINUTE.
>> HERE, PUT IT BETWEEN MY LEGS.
>> Jeff: YELLOW TEAM HAS MADE
VERY LITTLE PROGRESS
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
IF THIS WERE LIFE OR DEATH,
YOU'D BE DEAD.
(FABIO LAUGHS)
>> Y'ALL STAY FOCUSED.
>> Jeff: RAIN STARTING
TO COME DOWN NOW.
FABIO WILL BE FIRST
TO CROSS FOR THE BLUE TEAM.
>> DON'T JUMP! DON'T JUMP!
THAT ROLLS THE BARREL.
>> Jeff: BENRY STILL CAN'T
FIGURE IT OUT.
FABIO, PURPLE KELLY,
JANE, NAONKA,
AND CHASE WIN REWARD!
PIZZA, BROWNIES,
AND VOLCANO SURFING.
BENRY MAKES THE BEST MOVE IN THE
CHALLENGE FOR THE YELLOW TEAM
WITH THE CEREMONIAL LOSER
DISMOUNT.
>> MAN, WE WEREN'T EVEN CLOSE.
>> Jeff: BLUE TEAM,
CONGRATULATIONS.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO SPEND THE
AFTERNOON
DOING A LITTLE VOLCANO BOARDING.
YOU WILL THEN ENJOY HOT PIZZA,
CHOCOLATE BROWNIES,
AND SOME SOFT DRINKS.
SOUND LIKE A FUN AFTERNOON?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: I FORGOT TO TELL YOU
HOW YOU'RE GETTING THERE,
BY HELICOPTER.
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN ON A
HELICOPTER!
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN IN A
HELICOPTER AND I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D EVEN HAVE A PASSPORT IN THIS
LIFETIME
LET ALONE BE IN A HELICOPTER.
I'M BLOWN AWAY, BLOWN AWAY.
>> OH, LOOK AT THIS!
>> CHECK THIS OUT!
>> THAT'S A VOLCANO WAY OVER
THERE.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> NO WAY!
FLYING UP TO THE VOLCANO, IT WAS
SO AWESOME.
I DON'T THINK ANY OF US REALLY
EXPECTED IT
TO BE THAT BE BEAUTIFUL.
THAT IS AMAZING.
>> WE LAND ON THIS HUMONGOUS
BLACK MOUNTAIN,
AND IT WAS ALMOST LIKE YOU WERE
WALKING ON THE MOON.
YOU COULD SEE STEAM RISING UP,
AND YOU COULD JUST FEEL
THE HEAT COMING UP BETWEEN YOU
AND THE GROUND.
>> HOW ACTIVE DO YOU THINK THIS
THING IS?
>> ACTIVE.
>> AT THE CHALLENGE, JEFF HAD
MENTIONED VOLCANO SURFING
AS PART OF THE REWARD, SO WE'RE
ACTUALLY GOING TO BE CRUISING
DOWN THE SIDE OF THIS VOLCANO,
AND I'VE NEVER
EVEN HEARD OF THAT BEFORE.
THAT BLEW MY MIND, DUDE.
(indistinct yelling)
>> WOW, MAN!
>> DUDE!
>> THAT WAS CRAZY!
>> HEY, I'M HANGING WITH THE
KIDS NOW.
JUST BECAUSE I MAY BE A LITTLE
BIT OLDER THAN THEM,
I'M NOT AFRAID TO DO THIS.
>> LET'S GO, JANE!
>> GO, JANE!
>> YEAH!
>> THAT WAS FUN AS CRAP!
I LOVED IT.
I'VE RIDDEN ONE OF THOSE
ELECTRONIC BULLS, YOU KNOW,
AND THAT'S WHAT IT WAS LIKE,
RIDING A LITTLE BULL.
IT WAS AN EXPERIENCE I'LL NEVER
FORGET.
>> WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK'S
GOING DOWN AT CAMP.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> OH, MY GOD, GUYS.
OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> EVERYTHING BURNED.
>> ALL OF IT?
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS.
I'M GOING TO CRY.
>> LOOK AT THE MACHETES.
>> HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> NOT ONLY DID WE LOSE REWARD
CHALLENGE, BUT WE JUST GOT BACK
TO CAMP, AND PRETTY MUCH OUR
ENTIRE CAMP JUST BURNED DOWN.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS UN-FREAKING-BELIEVABLE.
WE'RE TRYING TO KEEP THIS DAMN
FIRE GOING DAY IN AND DAY OUT.
WE LEFT AND IT WAS RAINING SO WE
CREATED A LITTLE BARRICADE
WITH OUR THREE CHESTS, WOODEN
CHESTS, ONE OF WHICH HAD
ALL THE REST OF OUR FOOD IN IT.
>> YOU GUYS, DID WE REALLY BUILD
THAT FIRE UP THAT BIG?
>> YEAH.
>> LOOK HOW HOT IT WAS.
LOOK HOW THE GLASS MELTED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WE'RE LUCKY THE WHOLE THING
DIDN'T BURN DOWN.
>> WE LOST ALL OUR MACHETES.
ONLY THE BLADES ARE LEFT.
WE HAD OUR FLOUR.
WE HAD OUR MANGOS.
THERE WERE A COUPLE OF TOMATOES
LEFT.
THERE WAS AN EGGPLANT LEFT.
THAT WAS ALL BURNED DOWN,
AND NOW WE HAVE 10 PEOPLE WITH A
CUP OF RICE A DAY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'RE GOING TO
DO IT.
>> LOOK AT THE TARP.
IT MELTED.
>> THE TARP, WE CAN-- IT'S OKAY.
WE'LL JUST TURN IT AROUND.
>> THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE THIS?
>> IT'S NOT WORTH GETTING UPSET
ABOUT.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING THAT WE
HAVE-- IT'S ALREADY DONE.
WE HAVE TO CLEAN IT UP.
>> SOMEONE SHOULD PROBABLY WAKE
ME UP
AND TELL ME THAT THIS DID NOT
HAPPEN.
I MEAN, I GUESS ALL WE CAN DO IS
WRANGLE
WHAT WE HAVE LEFT AND KEEP IT
GOING.
BUT THIS IS A DAY FROM HELL.
>> I'M GOING TO HAVE A PIECE OF
EVERYTHING ON THIS TABLE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
25 DAYS, I HAVEN'T HAD
CHOCOLATE.
REWARD WAS AWESOME!
WE PIGGED OUT.
AND I MEAN, EVERYBODY PUT STUFF
ON THEIR PLATE.
I WOLFED DOWN A BROWNIE RIGHT
OFF THE BAT.
THEN HIT THE BANANA BREAD AND
PIZZA.
AND THEN I SUCKED DOWN ABOUT
THREE GLASSES OF SODA.
I COULD HAVE CARED LESS WHAT
THEY'RE DOING BACK AT CAMP
BECAUSE THAT WAS HEAVEN.
>> WHO DO YOU ALL THINK IS
RUNNING THE SHOW?
>> THAT IS WHAT'S SO UNCLEAR
AFTER EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED
YESTERDAY.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD TRY TO GET
A CONSENSUS HOW WE'RE FEELING
AND HOW OTHER PEOPLE ARE FEELING
BECAUSE IT'S GOING
TO MAKE TOMORROW EASIER.
>> COME HERE.
COME HERE.
>> WHY DID NAY TAKE HIM ASIDE.
>> NAY DOES THAT.
>> ON THE VOLCANO.
>> YOU NEVER TALK.
>> I KNOW, IT'S KIND OF FUNNY.
>> THAT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE,
BET YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> NO, THAT'S FOR REAL-FOR REAL.
>> THAT'S FOR REAL, THOUGH.
SHE'S SNEAKY AND SHE'S SITTING
SO COMFORTABLE RIGHT NOW CAUSE
SHE'S JUST TRYING
TO PICK EVERYBODY OFF
>> NAONKA PULLS ME ASIDE AND
SAYS WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER.
WE CAN GET BRENDA OUT OF HERE.
SHE'S RUNNING THE SHOW.
AND I'M THINKING, THIS IS GREAT.
IT JUST FELL RIGHT INTO MY HANDS
AND I'M TOTALLY GOING
TO MILK IT FOR ALL IT'S WORTH,
YOU KNOW.
AND HOPEFULLY I CAN STAY UNDER
THE RADAR
AND SLITHER THROUGH THINGS.
>> LIKE, I WANT BRENDA GONE
TOMORROW.
SHE WOULDN'T SEE THIS BLIND SIDE
COMING AT ALL.
>> WE CAN'T LET HER HEAR ABOUT
IT.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN SAYING
ANYTHING.
>> WHAT ABOUT CHASE?
>> DOES HE WANT HER OUT?
>> HE'S SO SCATTER BRAINED.
>> IF YOU GUYS ARE IN, I'M GOING
TO DO IT.
>> I'M IN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IN ORDER TO WIN THIS GAME,
YOU MUST MAKE POWER MOVES.
YOU CAN MAKE A BIG MOVE THAT CAN
SHIFT THE GAME
IN THE WHOLE OTHER DIRECTION,
BUT IF YOU MAKE A POWER MOVE,
YOU'RE MAKING A MOVE THAT WILL
PUSH YOU FORWARD, AND THE MORE
YOU KEEP MAKING THESE POWER
MOVES,
EVERYTHING'S JUST GOING TO FALL
IN LINE.
>> HOLLY'S FREAKING OUT.
>> SHE'S TRYING TO CHANGE THE
GAME UP RIGHT NOW.
>> OKAY.
>> WHEN I GOT BACK FROM THE
REWARD,
I WANTED TO TALK TO BRENDA.
I JUST DECIDED TO COME OUT AND
TELL HER, YOU KNOW, THE PLAN.
THAT THE OTHERS HAVE.
WELL, HERE'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
THERE'S THIS PLAN RIGHT NOW TO
TAKE YOU OUT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> IT'S HOLLY THAT'S
ORCHESTRATING IT.
HOLLY AND BEN, I THINK.
FOR WHATEVER REASON, I TRUST
BRENDA.
THAT'S ALL IT COMES DOWN TO IS I
TRUST HER AND I PUT MY GAME PLAN
IN HER AND, YOU KNOW, THERE IS
NO REASON OR RHYME.
IT'S JUST THE SIMPLE FACT THAT I
TRUST HER.
YOU KNOW, I'VE GONE WITH MY
HEART THIS ENTIRE GAME.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR ME TO TURN
AT THIS POINT AND BACKSTAB YOU.
THAT WOULD JUST MAKE ME LOOK
LIKE AN ASS.
>> COOL.
LUCKILY, I HAVE CHASE, WHO
TRUSTS ME 1,000%,
AND HE CAME AND TOLD ME THE
WHOLE PLAN.
IT IS A CHALLENGE RIGHT NOW.
BUT I STILL THINK THAT I DON'T
HAVE TO DO ANYTHING CRAZY
TO BEAT THEM.
LIKE, I'M NOT EVEN THAT
IMPRESSED.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
BRENDA?
>> SHE'S SHADY RIGHT NOW.
AND SHE HAS TOO MUCH POWER RIGHT
NOW.
>> BUT I DON'T THINK IT'S MOST
IMPORTANT
TO GET BRENDA OUT RIGHT NOW.
I THINK IT'S MOST IMPORTANT TO
GET BENRY.
>> WHOA, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
BENRY.
I THINK IT SHOULD BE BRENDA.
>> DO YOU TRUST HOLLY?
>> FOR NOW.
>> I DON'T RIGHT NOW.
HOLLY AND BENRY HAVE PUT
TOGETHER
THIS PLAN TO VOTE OUT BRENDA
NEXT.
AND I TOLD BRENDA THAT.
>> CHASE HAS BEEN RUNNING AROUND
HERE LIKE A CHICKEN
WITH HIS HEAD CUT OFF, TELLING
PEOPLE'S GAME PLANS.
LATELY, HE'S BEEN SO SCATTER
BRAINED
AND SO NERVOUS THAT I HAVE TO
FLOP.
I HAVE TO BE SMART.
I HAVE TO GO WITH HOLLY AND
JANE.
I HAVE TO GO WITH THE PEOPLE WHO
WANT
TO GET THE STRONG PEOPLE OUT.
IT'S THE SMART THING TO DO.
WE CANNOT TRUST CHASE.
>> REALLY?
>> WE CAN'T.
AND I KNOW THAT'S MIND BLOWING
AND IT SOUND LIKE I'M (\BLEEP\).
DO NOT TRUST HIM.
HE'S PLAYING BOTH IN THE MIDDLE.
HE WANTS YOU OUT NEXT.
>> REALLY?
WHAT DO WE DO.
>> WE HAVE TO GET BRENDA OUT, WE
HAVE TO GET SASH OUT
AND THEN GET CHASE OUT.
>> SO YOU'RE IN ON THIS.
CHASE IS CRAZY.
HE'S BEEN PLAYING WITH MIS HEART
AND EMOTION
THIS ENTIRE GAME SINCE DAY TWO.
HE IS BEING PLAYED BY BRENDA.
HOPEFULLY CHASE WILL GROW A PAIR
AND REALIZE WHAT'S GOOD FOR HIM.
>> CHASE IS TOTALLY
AGAINST GETTING
BRENDA OR SASH OUT.
>> YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> I AM SO-- JANE, LOOK AT ME.
I AM DEAD SERIOUS.
YOU CAN'T TRUST CHASE RIGHT NOW.
AND HE'S LIKE WIGGING OUT.
>> I ORIGINALLY TRUSTED CHASE,
BUT CHASE IS SUCKING UP
TO BRENDA LIKE HE WANTS TO GET
IN HER PANTS OR SOMETHING.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT KIND OF
MAGIC SPELL SHE'S CASTING OVER
CHASE RIGHT NOW, BUT IF THAT BIG
OLD COUNTRY BOY WANTS TO GO BACK
ON HIS WORD, HE'S GOING TO CATCH
HELL WHEN HE GETS BACK
TO CAROLINA BECAUSE CAROLINA
PEOPLE DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> YOU CANNOT TRUST CHASE.
>> I TOLD YOU.
>> YOU CANNOT.
YOU JUST CAN'T.
>> I KNEW IT.
>> HE'S NOT GOING TO VOTE FOR
BRENDA.
>> DOESN'T HE SEE THAT BRENDA
AND SASH
ARE IN TOTAL CHARGE OF THIS
GAME?
>> YEAH, HE SEES IT BUT HE'S
STUPID.
>> WHAT THE ...
IS WRONG WITH CHASE?
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
BRENDA, I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU'RE GOING TO STAND
ON A VERY SMALL PLATFORM
OVER THE WATER.
YOU'LL LEAN BACK
HOLDING ON TO A ROPE.
EVERY FIVE MINUTES,
YOU'LL MOVE YOUR HANDS
FURTHER DOWN THE ROPE,
MAKING IT MORE DIFFICULT.
WHEN YOU CAN'T
HOLD ON ANY LONGER,
YOU'LL FALL IN THE WATER,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING
WINS IMMUNITY
AND IS GUARANTEED A 1-IN-9 SHOT
AT A MILLION DOLLARS.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY MOVE YOUR
HANDS DOWN TO THAT FIRST KNOT.
WE'RE LOOKING GOOD.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
FOR IMMUNITY.
AND A SINGLE-DIGIT SHOT
AT A MILLION DOLLARS.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU DO NOT PUT
YOUR HANDS ABOVE THAT TOP KNOT.
>> AAHH!
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY
STRUGGLING.
SASH IS FIRST IN THE WATER.
SASH IS FIRST OUT.
FOLLOWED RIGHT BEHIND
BY PURPLE KELLY.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO EIGHT.
BRENDA NOW STRUGGLING A LITTLE.
HOLLY IN THE WATER.
HOLLY'S THIRD OUT.
DAN STRUGGLING
AND A NICE RECOVERY.
USING THOSE GUNS!
YOU WORKED HARD FOR THOSE GUNS!
BRENDA IS OUT.
DAN IS OUT.
FABIO'S HAD ENOUGH.
HE RELEASES.
WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
KEEP DIGGING.
YOU DO NOT WANT
TO GO HOME TONIGHT.
YOU DO NOT WANT TO GO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WITHOUT IMMUNITY
AROUND YOUR NECK.
BENRY DIGGING DEEP.
NAONKA DROPS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE NOW.
CHASE, JANE, AND BENRY.
LOOK AT THAT.
THE OLDEST WOMAN IN THIS GAME
GOING UP AGAINST TWO OF THE
YOUNGEST AND MOST FIT GUYS,
SHOWING NO SIGNS OF STRAIN.
>> WIN ONE FOR
THE OLD GUYS, JANIE.
>> I'M TRYING, BUDDY.
>> COME ON, HONEY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING
TO MOVE DOWN TO THE NEXT KNOT.
>> AARRGG!
AAHH!
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
YOU HAVE FIVE SECONDS
TO GET THERE.
MAKE YOUR MOVE.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
THERE WE GO.
YOU GUYS ARE DOING GREAT.
DIG DEEP.
RIGHT NOW, THINK ONLY ABOUT
HOLDING ON TO THIS ROPE.
DON'T THINK ABOUT ANYTHING ELSE.
KEEP HOLDING ON.
AND WHEN YOU'RE TIRED,
FIND MORE STRENGTH.
FIND SOMETHING ELSE.
GO DEEPER.
BENRY IS OUT,
AND WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
>> GOOD JOB, BEN.
>> GOOD JOB, BENRY.
>> Jeff: WE ARE DOWN
TO CHASE AND JANE,
ARGUABLY THE MOST FIT
GUY OUT HERE
GOING AGAINST THE OLDEST WOMAN
IN THIS GAME.
A GREAT MATCH-UP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HOWEVER YOU FEEL JANE,
BUT I'M STAYING ON HERE.
>> WELL, MY FINGERS ARE
ABOUT READY TO GO.
>> I'M PRETTY SECURE.
>> I'M GONNA LET GO.
>> Jeff: WHY ARE YOU
GOING TO LET GO?
>> MY FINGERS ARE CRAMPING.
>> COME ON, JANE.
>> Jeff: JANE, DIG.
DON'T YOU DARE GIVE UP
ON THIS CHALLENGE!
BOTH YOU GUYS.
YOU'VE DONE TOUGHER THAN THIS.
KEEP FIGHTING.
>> HANG IN THERE, JANE.
>> SHIFT YOUR WEIGHT AROUND.
CHASE IS OUT.
JANE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
>> GOOD JOB, JANE!
GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: YOU EARNED
A LITTLE HELP.
>> OH, CRAZY.
>> I'M GLAD I LIFT
80-POUND DOGS.
>> GOOD WORK.
>> CRAZY.
>> Jeff: HOW CLOSE WERE YOU
TO FALLING OFF?
>> MY PINKIES WERE, LIKE,
CRUSHED.
>> Jeff:
YOU HUNG IN LONG ENOUGH
TO OUT-LAST CHASE,
IMMUNITY TONIGHT.
YOU'RE STILL SHAKING.
YOU WON'T BE SHAKING TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU ARE SAFE TONIGHT.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME.
GET YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
GOOD WORK.
>> MAN! I WANTED
TO WIN SO BAD!
AND TO GET BEAT BY JANE!
PROPS TO HER.
SHE'S GOT SOME SERIOUS
SUPERWOMAN STRENGTH
DEEP INSIDE OF HER.
(birds squawking)
>> OH.
>> GOOD JOB, JANE.
>> THAT WAS A LOT HARDER
THAN IT LOOKED. >> A LOT HARDER.
>> WINNING IMMUNITY WAS GREAT.
I FEEL ON TOP OF THE WORLD
RIGHT NOW.
I KNEW IF IT WAS ANYTHING
PHYSICALLY
THAT HAD TO DO WITH MY HANDS,
I WOULD DO OKAY,
'CAUSE WHEN YOU'RE FIGHTING A
DOG TRYING TO GO THEIR TOENAILS,
YOU'VE GOT
TO HAVE A REAL GOOD GRIP,
SO I'M REALLY HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
AND I THINK, UNLESS SHE ENDS UP
WITH AN IDOL AND PLAYS IT,
BRENDA WILL GO HOME.
(hooting)
>> OKAY. COOL.
SO WHO DO WE TARGET FIRST?
>> I MEAN, THEY'RE OUR THREATS.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY THINK
ABOUT TAKING ONE OF THEM OUT
NEXT, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, BENRY, RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I THINK BENRY'S
THE BIGGEST THREAT AROUND HERE.
>> I SAY WE STICK WITH THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> I PERSONALLY THINK
WE SHOULD VOTE BENRY OUT FIRST.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO PLAY
THIS GAME WITH PEOPLE I TRUST,
AND RIGHT NOW,
I DON'T TRUST BENRY.
SO, I'M TRYING
TO PROTECT BRENDA,
BUT WE MAY NOT HAVE THE NUMBERS
TO DO IT.
(birds squawking)
>> HE DRIVES ME CRAZY.
>> HE DRIVES ME NUTS.
YESTERDAY HE PISSED ME OFF TO
THE HIGHEST POINT OF PISS-IVITY.
>> YEAH.
>> MM.
>> YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON? >> WHAT?
>> WE'RE TRYING
TO VOTE BRENDA OUT TONIGHT.
AND ME AND YOU COULD MAKE
A HUGE POWER MOVE.
AND IT'S GONNA BE SO EASY
TO GET PEOPLE TO TURN ON HER.
>> I KNOW. >> BECAUSE
THEY SEE HER AS A THREAT.
>> IF YOU WOULD HAVE ASKED ME
A FEW DAYS AGO,
I'D SAY THAT BRENDA HELD A LOT
OF CARDS IN THIS GAME.
BUT NOW,
TIDES HAVE TURNED A LITTLE BIT,
AND THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
IN THE GAME
THAT I'M STARTING
TO WORRY A LITTLE BIT.
>> YOU'RE COMING TO ME STRAIGHT,
RIGHT? >> YEAH.
>> SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THE WHOLE THING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
'CAUSE I'VE TRIED TO...
I'VE SAT BACK AND NOT REALLY...
>> I JUST THINK BRENDA'S BEEN
THE RING LEADER.
>> SHE WAS THE RING LEADER
OVER AT YOUR CAMP. >> YEAH.
>> SHE'S THE RING LEADER HERE.
SHE'S JUST...
SHE'S GOT EVERYBODY ON HER LIST,
AND THAT'S HOW
THEY'RE GOING TO GO.
SO, THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> YEAH. I'VE BEEN PLAYING
THIS GAME WITH MY HEART
AND NOT MY HEAD A LOT
OF THE TIME,
AND IT ABSOLUTELY KILLS ME THAT
I MIGHT HAVE TO VOTE BRENDA OUT.
I DON'T TRUST BENRY.
I DON'T TRUST HOLLY
ALL THAT MUCH.
DAN-- I DON'T REALLY TRUST HIM.
NAY-- I DON'T TRUST HER ANYMORE.
SO, IF BRENDA'S GONE,
I'M PLAYING THE GAME WITH PEOPLE
THAT I DON'T REALLY TRUST.
THAT'S A...
THAT'S A SCARY THOUGHT.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE SAYING YOU.
I DON'T KNOW IF THERE'S
ANY NUMBERS TO SAVE YOU.
THE THING THAT CHANGED WAS NAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
NAY'S NOT GONNA VOTE FOR ME.
>> NAY SWEARS
SHE'S VOTING FOR YOU.
NAY WAS... NAY'S THE ONE
THAT SCREWED IT UP.
IT SURE AS HELL WASN'T MY IDEA.
>> HMM.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE IS OPERATION
TAKE-OUT-BRENDA IN PLACE.
I'M PRETTY ANNOYED ABOUT IT,
BUT I THINK
ALL I CAN DO IS STAY COOL.
THE LAST THING I WANT TO DO IS
START SCRAMBLING.
IT JUST SHOWS
THAT YOU'RE DESPERATE.
SO, YOU KNOW,
IF I SHOW CONFIDENCE,
MY FRIENDS
HAVE CONFIDENCE IN ME.
IT SHOWS THAT, YEAH, I KIND OF
WANT TO STICK WITH BRENDA.
>> TELL HER WHO MESSED
THE FIVE OF US FIRST?
>> NAONKA?
>> EXACTLY.
>> BUT HOW?
>> SHE WANTS YOU OUT.
>> I TRUSTED HER 1,000%.
>> ME, TOO.
>> BUT THEN, NOW WHAT?
NONE OF THOSE PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO BE LOYAL TO YOU.
THEY SAW THE ALLIANCE, AND NOW
THEY'RE BREAKING IT, THOUGH,
SO, YOU THINK
THEY'RE GOING TO SAVE YOU?
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
MAYBE YOU BLINDSIDE THEM
WITH YOUR IMMUNITY IDOL.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
BECAUSE IF I GET VOTED OUT
TONIGHT,
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU CAN GET THE NUMBERS BACK.
>> THE IDOL IS DEFINITELY
SOMETHING TO BE USED
TO NOT ONLY TO PROTECT YOURSELF,
BUT ALSO SOMEONE
WITHIN YOUR ALLIANCE.
MY GOAL WOULD BE TO NEVER
HAVE TO USE IT AT ALL.
HOWEVER, AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THE MOMENT CAME UP
WHERE I NEEDED TO USE IT
TO SAVE BRENDA,
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO CONSIDER
VERY STRONGLY DOING THAT.
>> YOU DON'T THINK SASH IS GOING
TO GIVE BRENDA THE IDOL?
>> HELL, NO.
>> I'M JUST FURIOUS THAT NAONKA
WOULD MAKE SUCH A DUMB MOVE.
I THOUGHT
WE HAD A GREAT ALLIANCE.
I REALLY BELIEVED
THAT WE WOULD GO TO THE END.
BUT NOW I DON'T EVEN WANT TO SEE
NAONKA'S FACE.
I WANTED TO TAKE OUT BENRY,
BUT, HOPEFULLY, SASH IS GOING
TO GIVE ME HIS IMMUNITY IDOL,
AND WE BLINDSIDE NAONKA.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING
IN THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ALINA AND MARTY, VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SASH, WERE YOU SURPRISED
AT THE LAST VOTE
WHEN MARTY WAS SENT HOME?
>> YEAH, I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE
WERE SURPRISED,
BUT SINCE
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THERE'S BEEN A LOT
OF RESHUFFLING IN THE TRIBE,
AND SO, I THINK
I'M MORE OUT OF THE LOOP NOW
THAN I'VE BEEN
SINCE THE GAME STARTED.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff:
CHASE, DO YOU BELIEVE
SASH BELIEVES
HE'S OUT OF THE LOOP?
>> I DO, BECAUSE
HE HAD A STRONG ALLIANCE,
AND NOW THAT STRONG ALLIANCE
SEEMS TO BE GO GONE.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, ANY REGRETS
OVER THE LAST VOTE?
>> YEAH. I DIDN'T WANT
TO VOTE MARTY.
ALL MY PEEPS KNOW IT,
BUT I HAD TO PROVE SOMETHING
TO PEOPLE
WHO WERE IN MY ALLIANCE
THAT THEY COULD TRUST ME.
>> Jeff: HOW HARD IS IT FOR YOU
TO TRUST PEOPLE OUT HERE?
>> NOT HARD.
I'VE NEVER HAD A PROBLEM
WITH THAT FROM THE START.
AND I THOUGHT
THAT THERE WAS
A REALLY STRONG CORE ALLIANCE,
THE STRONGEST ONE
IN THIS WHOLE GAME.
I KNOW THAT FOR A FACT.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW IS
THERE'S A BREAK IN THE ALLIANCE
BECAUSE OF
NAONKA WANTING TO JUMP SHIP,
AND THIS IS
THE MOST SURPRISING THING
BECAUSE I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT THESE GUYS RIGHT HERE.
MEANWHILE, SHE'S THE ONE
THAT WANTS TO GO.
>> Jeff: NAONKA, THAT'S A PRETTY
STRAIGHT-OUT ACCUSATION.
>> I DON'T THINK IT WAS ME, TO
BE HONEST WITH YOU. I THINK...
>> Jeff: HOLD ON.
YOU DON'T THINK IT WAS YOU?
>> IT WAS NOT ME, OKAY?
EVERYBODY COULD PUT IT ON ME,
BUT I'LL PUT IT LIKE THIS.
CHASE WAS RUNNING AROUND
YESTERDAY WITH HIS HEAD CUT OFF.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT CHASE DOES.
HE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
HE WAS PARANOID.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE TELLING
BRENDA RIGHT NOW,
"IT WASN'T ME."
>> IT WAS NOT ME.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT
TO FOLLOW YOUR INTUITION
IN THIS GAME, BUT...
>> CAN I GET IN ON THIS?
>> IT WAS NOT ME.
>> I DID GO TO BRENDA
BECAUSE I TRUSTED HER.
SO THIS IS NO NEW NEWS
TO ANYBODY.
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY,
WEIGH IN ON THIS.
GIVE US 20 YEARS OF WISDOM.
>> WELL, LET ME TELL YOU,
20 YEARS OF WISDOM.
I THINK THAT...
WELL, I THINK THAT
THIS IS THE FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL
I FELT COMPLETELY
OUT OF THE LOOP
ON WHAT'S GOING ON,
TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST.
>> Jeff: HAVE YOU BEEN LEARNING
STUFF TONIGHT?
>> YES, COMPLETELY!
LIKE, MY WHOLE... MY...
THE WHEELS ARE TURNING
IN MY HEAD.
MY GAME PLAN, IT'S... I'M...
LIKE, THIS... IT'S ENLIGHTENING.
>> Jeff: SO, BRENDA, YOU'VE
HEARD A LOT OF PEOPLE TALKING.
NOW WHERE DO YOU SIT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENED?
>> WHY WOULD SASH BREAK UP
THE BEST ALLIANCE HERE
'CAUSE HE'S SO SMART?
AND WHY WOULD CHASE LET ME IN
ON IT THE DAY BEFORE?
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO TELL ME.
SO THEN, IT MAKES SENSE THAT IT
WAS NAONKA WANTING TO JUMP SHIP.
THAT MAKES MORE SENSE TO ME.
>> Jeff: WHAT HAPPENS, SASH,
IF YOU BREAK TRUST IN THIS GAME?
WHAT DO YOU PUT AT RISK?
>> THAT YOU MAY GET SENT HOME.
I THINK THE PEOPLE HERE
THAT REALLY KNOW ME KNOW
THAT I AM TRUSTWORTHY,
AND THAT'S THE ONLY REASON WHY
I MADE IT TO THE MERGE,
AND HOPEFULLY, THAT'S WHY
I'LL STICK AROUND
FOR ANOTHER TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: SO, BRENDA,
DID YOU SCRAMBLE THIS AFTERNOON?
>> I DID LITTLE THINGS
THAT I THINK WOULD HELP.
I KNEW THAT IF I HAD A CHANCE,
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE WITH CHASE
AND WITH SASH,
AND IF I TALKED WITH BOTH
OF THEM,
TO MAKE THEM SEE, LIKE,
WHAT THE HELL?,
MAYBE THEY WOULD SWITCH.
THE REST IS, LIKE, "OKAY, YEAH,
THEY'LL VOTE FOR ME, WHATEVER."
BUT THAT WAS MY PLAN.
>> Jeff: SO, BRENDA,
YOU WOULD ARGUE
THAT YOU WERE TRYING
TO STAY IN THIS GAME, EVEN NOW.
>> JUST NOT SCRAMBLING, YEAH.
>> Jeff: WHAT IS IT
ABOUT THE WORD "SCRAMBLING?"
ARE YOU TOO PROUD FOR THAT WORD?
>> I THINK SO.
IT'S THE TRUTH.
I JUST FEEL LIKE
THERE ARE BETTER OPTIONS,
AND THERE'S A DIFFERENT WAY
TO DO THINGS.
>> Jeff: SO SCRAMBLING IS
BENEATH YOU?
>> IT'S JUST NOT MY STYLE.
>> IN MY OPINION, I THINK
IF PEOPLE SEE YOU SCRAMBLING,
THEY SEE YOU
AS IF YOU'VE ALREADY LOST.
"LOOK AT HER, SHE'S SCRAMBLING.
LOOK AT THAT.
ISN'T SHE FUNNY?
DON'T YOU FEEL BAD FOR HER?"
WHO CAN I REALLY CHANGE HERE?
IT'S THE PEOPLE THAT I'VE BEEN
TALKING TO THIS WHOLE TIME.
I TALK TO YOU ONE-ON-ONE,
I LOOK AT YOU IN THE EYE,
AND YOU KNOW THAT I'M REAL.
>> Jeff: SASH, YOU GOT
TO BE SHAKING IN YOUR BOOTS.
THIS IS DISASTROUS FOR ANYBODY
WHO HAD AN ALLIANCE.
'CAUSE RIGHT NOW, THIS...
IT'S LIKE A LITTLE BOMB JUST
DROPPED IN HERE AND BA-BOOM!
>> I THINK
SINCE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
EVERYONE'S ALLIANCES
HAVE CHANGED A BIT.
AND PEOPLE HAVE A MUCH DIFFERENT
OUTLOOK IN THE GAME NOW
THAN THEY DID
JUST A COUPLE OF DAYS AGO,
AND SOMETIMES YOU HAVE
TO MAKE CHANGES ACCORDINGLY.
>> Jeff:
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE
THERE ARE A COUPLE
OF DIFFERENT PHILOSOPHIES
ABOUT WHAT IT TAKES
TO KEEP YOURSELF IN THIS GAME.
LET'S SEE HOW IT PLAYS OUT.
JANE,
YOU HAVE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
I KNOW YOU'RE KEEPING IT.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR JANE.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DAN, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE SCRAMBLED.
>> YOU ARE MY REAL, TRUE ENEMY,
AND I THOUGHT
YOU WERE MY FRIEND.
>> Jeff:
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE-- BRENDA.
NAONKA.
BENRY. ONE VOTE BRENDA,
ONE VOTE BENRY, ONE VOTE NAONKA.
BRENDA.
THAT'S TWO VOTES BRENDA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES BRENDA,
ONE VOTE BENRY, ONE VOTE NAONKA.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES BRENDA.
ELEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT
AND THE THIRD MEMBER
OF OUR JURY-- BRENDA.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
BRENDA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff:
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, IF THERE'S ONE THING
TO BE LEARNED IT'S THIS.
IF YOU WANT TO WIN THIS GAME
AND THE MILLION DOLLARS
THAT GOES WITH IT,
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGHT FOR IT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:
NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR...
NAONKA'S ANTICS HAVE THE TRIBE
IN AN UPROAR.
>> I WAS JUST SHOCKED
THAT NAONKA WOULD DO SOMETHING
SO STUPID.
>> NAONKA OBVIOUSLY WASN'T
THINKING STRAIGHT.
WE'VE GOT TO GET HER OUT NOW.
>> IF ONE OF THE GUYS HAD DONE
THAT, I WOULD HAVE TOLD THEM
TO JUST GET THE ... OUT OF HERE
AND DON'T COME BACK.
>> I'M STILL IN DISBELIEF,
REALLY, AT HOW OUTPLAYED I WAS
BY THE PERSON
THAT I TRUSTED THE MOST, NAONKA.
IT'S JUST FUNNY HOW THE GAME
CHANGED SO FAST FOR ME.
ONE DAY I WAS AT THE TOP,
AND NOW, I'M OUT.
IT WAS A CRAZY GAME
THAT I-I DIDN'T EXPECT WOULD END
SO SOON FOR ME,
BUT, UM, I AM KIND OF SAD
THAT IT'S OVER.