>> Jeff Probst:
PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR:
>> REPLACE YOUR OLD BUFFS WITH
THESE NEW ONES.
YOU HAVE MERGED.
>> Jeff: AFTER THE MERGE, BRENDA
AND SASH WERE CALLING THE SHOTS.
>> WE'RE THE TWO MOST POWERFUL
PEOPLE IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: MARTY WAS AT THE TOP OF
THEIR HIT LIST.
>> MARTY IS SOMEBODY TO WATCH
BECAUSE HE'S IS TALKING TO BENRY
AND FABIO AND DAN.
>> HURRY UP, GET YOUR BAG,
AND WE'RE GOING TO WALK.
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING BLEW UP
WHEN NAONKA TOOK ALINA
ON A FOOD-STEALING MISSION.
THE TRIBE FOUND OUT
AND WANTED NAONKA'S HEAD.
>> THAT'S REALLY UNCOOL.
>> Jeff: BUT SASH AND BRENDA
WANTED TO PROTECT HER
SO THEY OFFERED UP
ALINA INSTEAD.
>> IT SUCKS TO BE ALINA
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: BUT MARTY GOT PARANOID
AND THOUGHT HE WAS
THE NEXT TO GO.
SO AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
MARTY TRIED TO SAVE HIMSELF
BY THROWING JANE UNDER THE BUS.
>> YOU LET THE LITTLE OLD LADY
FROM SOUTH CAROLINA...
>> NORTH CAROLINA.
>> THIS LADY WILL
TAKE THE MILLION DOLLARS.
>> Jeff: NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT
AND THE FIRST MEMBER
OF OUR JURY.
ALINA WAS VOTED OUT.
ALINA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW THE FEUD BETWEEN JANE AND
MARTY HAS REACHED CRITICAL MASS.
11 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT?
>> HEY, YOU GUYS,
HAND ME YOUR TORCHES.
RIGHT HERE.
>> TRIBAL WAS THE WORST.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL IS WHERE
YOU NEED TO VENT,
BUT I THINK THAT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL REALLY SHOOK THINGS UP.
I FELT REALLY BAD FOR JANE.
MARTY, HE WAS GOING A LITTLE
TOO HARD ON HER, YOU KNOW,
LIKE HE'S THROWING PUNCHES
BUT SHE CAN'T BLOCK.
THE ONLY THING SHE CAN DO
IS JUST TAKE IT
AND TAKE IT AND TAKE IT
AND TAKE IT.
AND I THINK SHE DID WELL,
BECAUSE IF THE SHOE WAS ON THE
OTHER FOOT AND IT WAS ME,
I WOULD HAVE WENT
RIGHT BACK AT HIM
AND HIT HIM REALLY,
REALLY, HARD.
>> THAT'S JUST HOW HE IS.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
>> WELL, WAIT TILL
HE ATTACKS YOU, HONEY.
>> I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> THE JACKASS NAMED MR. FARTY--
IS GONNA BE HIS NAME FROM NOW
ON, INSTEAD OF "MARTY,"
IN MY BOOK--
IS A JACKASS TO TRY
TO ATTACK ME.
I PERSONALLY DON'T THINK
HE CAN BEAT ME PHYSICALLY,
MUCH LESS MENTALLY.
I'M STILL GOING TO PLAY MY GAME
THE WAY I'M PLAYING IT,
BUT I THINK HE'S
GRASPING AT STRAWS
BECAUSE HE KNOWS
HIS DAYS ARE NUMBERED.
♪ ♪
>> DO YOU THINK IT WAS CHASE
THAT PUT MY NAME DOWN?
NOT THAT IT REALLY MATTERS
BUT IT'S JUST GOOD TO KNOW.
DO YOU THINK IT WAS CHASE,
OR DO YOU THINK IT WAS HOLLY?
>> I THINK IT WAS HOLLY.
>> OKAY, THEN, THAT TELLS ME
THAT CHASE HAS GOT
MAYBE HALF A BRAIN.
IT'S JUST FRUSTRATING TO PLAY
A GAME WITH PEOPLE,
SOME PEOPLE THAT
ARE JUST STUPID.
I FEEL LIKE I CLEARED
THE AIR LAST NIGHT.
I WAS VERY, VERY CRYSTAL CLEAR
THAT I THINK EVERYBODY
UNDERESTIMATES
HOW DANGEROUS JANE IS
IN THIS GAME.
BUT THERE IS NO QUESTION THAT
I'M POTENTIALLY IN TROUBLE HERE.
I'VE GOT A BIG TARGET ON MY BACK
SO I FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO HAVE A BUTTON-DOWN PLAN
BETWEEN NOW AND NEXT TRIBAL
OR THEY WILL ELIMINATE ME
IN A HEARTBEAT.
>> MARTY WAS TRYING TO POISON
EVERYBODY'S OPINION OF ME
BECAUSE HE KNOWS THERE'S NOOSE
AROUND HIS NECK.
HE'S JUST WAITING FOR THE
HATCHET MAN TO CUT THAT ROPE
AND HE'S GOING TO BE HUNG.
I'M TELLING YOU,
THE MAN SCRAMBLES
LIKE NOBODY I'VE EVER SEEN.
I MIGHT TAKE HIM TO THE WOOD
SHED AND WHIP HIS ASS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU WILL BE RANDOMLY DIVIDED
INTO TWO TEAMS.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL MAKE YOUR WAY
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES
WORKING TOGETHER TO COLLECT
THREE KEYS.
ONCE YOU'VE CLEARED
ALL THE OBSTACLES,
YOU WILL USE THE THREE KEYS
TO OPEN THREE LOCKS.
FIRST TEAM TO RAISE THEIR FLAG
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TEAM WILL
BE TAKEN TO A BEAUTIFUL SPOT
WHERE YOU WILL ENJOY
A CANOPY TOUR.
YOU'LL ZIPLINE
ACROSS THE TREETOPS,
EXPERIENCING NICARAGUA
IN A WHOLE NEW WAY.
WHEN THE TOUR IS OVER,
YOU'LL TREAT YOURSELVES
TO A SURVIVOR BARBECUE:
CHICKEN, STEAK,
POTATO CHIPS, APPLE PIE.
>> APPLE PIE!
>> Jeff: SOFT DRINKS
AND COLD BEER.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: WE'LL DRAW FOR TEAMS
AND GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE RANDOMLY DREW
FOR TEAMS, AND AMAZINGLY,
WE ENDED UP WITH
MEN VERSUS WOMEN.
BECAUSE WE HAVE 11 PEOPLE,
ONE OF YOU WAS NOT SELECTED.
CHASE, YOU WILL NOT RUN
IN THIS CHALLENGE,
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT YOU'RE OUT OF IT.
YOU'RE GOING TO CHOOSE
ONE TEAM TO BACK.
IF YOU CHOOSE THE RIGHT TEAM
AND THEY WIN, YOU GO ON REWARD.
OTHERWISE, YOU HEAD BACK TO CAMP
WITH THE LOSERS.
>> CHASE!
>> I'M GOING TO DO SOMETHING
CRAZY AND GO WITH THE GIRLS.
>> Jeff: CHASE, TAKE A SPOT
AT THE END OF THE RACE.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
MAKE YOUR WAY THROUGH THAT HAY.
>> OVER, OVER, OVER!
>> Jeff: KEEP MOVING, WOMEN.
DON'T CRAWL.
LET'S GO!
FABIO'S OUT FOR THE MEN.
ALL OF THE WOMEN
ARE OUT AT ONCE.
WORKING TOGETHER.
START ON THAT KEY.
>> COME ON, JANE, GET UP.
>> GO, GO, JANE, GET ON MY BACK.
>> Jeff: FABIO WORKING FOR
THE MEN, JANE FOR THE WOMEN.
JANE HAS IT FIRST.
FABIO RIGHT BEHIND.
WORKING THROUGH THAT
CRAWL-THROUGH.
>> COME ON, GET ON THE MAT.
>> Jeff: WE'RE DEAD EVEN.
GO! HIT IT!
HIT IT!
RUN BACK AND HIT IT AGAIN!
THE MEN ARE THROUGH
THE STICKS FIRST.
BRENDA IS UP AND OVER
AND THAT'S IT.
GO!
THAT WORKS! GO!
FABIO HAS THE SECOND KEY
FOR THE MEN.
THE WOMEN STILL IN IT.
>> COME ON, DANNY!
>> Jeff: WOMEN HOISTING JANE UP.
GOTTA GET THAT SECOND KEY.
LET'S GO!
>> GET ME UP!
>> Jeff: MEN ARE WORKING THEIR
WAY THROUGH THE NET CRAWL.
DAN SLOWING THE MEN DOWN.
LADIES, YOU'RE STILL IN THIS.
GO, WOMEN, GO, GO, GO!
YOU'RE STILL IN IT.
THEY'RE STILL ON THE NET CRAWL.
>> WE'RE IN THIS, COME ON,
BARBEQUE, BABY!
>> COME ON, DANNY!
>> Jeff: THE MEN ARE
THROUGH THE NET CRAWL
WORKING FOR THEIR THIRD KEY.
KEEP MOVING WOMEN.
LET'S GO, JANE.
PICK IT UP.
YOU'VE GOT IT IN YOU!
THE MEN HAVE THEIR THIRD KEY AND
THEY'RE THROUGH THE BRICK WALL.
>> COME ON, JANE!
>> Jeff: JANE WEARING DOWN
BUT NOT GIVING UP.
HUSTLE, JANE.
>> COME ON, JANE!
>> Jeff: THE MEN ARE THROUGH
THE SECOND BRICK WALL.
>> COME ON, GIRLS!
DON'T GIVE UP!
>> Jeff: JANE HURLS HERSELF DOWN
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> COME ON, JANE!
>> Jeff: THE MEN ARE NOW WORKING
ON THEIR LOCKS.
JANE ABSOLUTELY EXHAUSTED.
>> THEY'RE HARD TO TURN, GUYS.
>> COME ON, GIRLS,
COME ON, GIRLS!
>> GET UP!
>> COME ON, GIRLS!
>> THE OTHER WAY.
>> LET'S GO, THEY'RE MESSING UP,
THEY'RE MESSING UP.
LET'S GO, FINISH!
>> Jeff: THE WOMEN ARE NOT
GIVING UP, WORKING TOGETHER,
NAONKA NOW GOING FOR THE KEY.
>> Jeff: THE MEN HAVE
ONE LOCK UNDONE.
TWO LOCKS UNDONE.
>> LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: WOMEN HIT
THE BRICK WALL.
>> COME ON, GIRLS!
COME ON, GIRLS!
>> Jeff: THE MEN WIN REWARD!
>> OH, YEAH!
OH, YEAH!
BARBECUE!
ALL RIGHT, GREAT EFFORT
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
"SURVIVOR" IS
AN UNPREDICTABLE GAME.
NOBODY COULD HAVE EVER GUESSED
WE WOULD END UP
WITH MEN VERSUS WOMEN ON THIS
CHALLENGE.
PURPLE KELLY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> MAN, I AM HUNGRY.
IT'S JUST ROUGH.
>> SHE'LL BE OKAY.
>> I'M GREAT.
I GET TO SPEND THE AFTERNOON
WITH SOME AWESOME GIRLS AND
CHASE.
>> Jeff: CHASE BELIEVED IN YOU.
>> THAT SAYS A LOT ABOUT CHASE.
>> Jeff: SO, GUYS, I HAVE A
QUESTION FOR YOU.
IN THIS SOCIAL GAME IN WHICH IT
IS ALL ABOUT RELATIONSHIPS
AND GETTING VOTES AT THE END, IS
THERE ANY ONE GUY
WHO FEELS YOU KNOW WHAT?
SOMEBODY OVER THERE WORKED HARD
ENOUGH, THEY DESERVE MY SPOT.
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT UP?
>> I DON'T THINK SO, JEFF.
>> NO.
I NEED TO EAT.
>> Jeff: SO, WE HAVE 11
INDIVIDUALS PLAYING THIS GAME.
WHATEVER ALLIANCES EXIST, THEY
AREN'T EXISTING RIGHT NOW,
NOT WITH A BARBECUE ON THE LINE.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU ARE GOING TO ENJOY A FUN
AFTERNOON.
YOU'RE GOING TO ZIPLINE ACROSS
THE TREETOPS.
WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED, YOU WILL
HAVE A GREAT BARBECUE.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GRAB YOUR
STUFF.
HEAD OUT AND ENJOY.
ALL RIGHT, WOMEN, IN SPITE OF
REALLY GREAT EFFORT,
I GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
CHASE, YOU'RE GOING WITH THEM.
>> CHASE SELECTING TO STAY WITH
THE GIRLS,
WHY WOULD YOU EVER DO THAT?
IT'S LIKE WATCHING CHASE JOIN
JANE WAS LIKE WATCHING THE MOVIE
"DUMB AND DUMBER."
I DON'T GET IT.
>> WHOOO!
>> WHOOO-HOOO!
>> LET IT RIP, BENRY!
>> NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS DID
I THINK I'D BE IN NICARAGUA,
ZIPPING ACROSS THE JUNGLE ON A
ZIPLINE.
AND I COULDN'T HAVE ASKED FOR A
BETTER FOUR GUYS TO BE WITH.
IT WAS A DAY FOR THE BOYS.
>> GO, DANNY!
>> COME ON, DANNY BOY!
LET IT RIP, DANNY!
LET IT GO!
>> THE FIRST TIME FLYING ABOVE
THE NICARAGUAN JUNGLE
ON THE ZIPLINE, IT WAS OKAY.
THERE AREN'T ANY ZIPLINES IN
BROOKLYN.
IF THERE ARE, YOU'RE A BURGLAR.
>> DANNY, HOW COOL WAS THAT?
>> CRAZY.
>> OH, LOOK AT THIS ONE RIGHT
HERE.
>> THIS IS A GOOD ONE.
>> THIS IS A BANGER.
A BIG ONE.
>> IT FELT INCREDIBLE, ALMOST
SYMBOLICALLY, TO BE HOOKED
ONTO A ZIPLINE IN MIDAIR ABOVE
THE JUNGLE ENJOYING A DAY OFF.
IT WAS THRILLING, EXHILARATING,
AND...
I FELT FREE.
YEAH, MARTY!
>> WHOOO!
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> COME ON, DANNY BOY!
>> WHOOO-HOOO!
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> WOW!
>> WHOOO-HOOO!
>> TAKING THIS THING TO THE END,
MAN.
>> WE EARNED IT!
>> NICE JOB TODAY, MAN.
>> THE BEST PART OF THE BARBECUE
IS GETTING A LITTLE OPPORTUNITY
TO SPEAK TO THE GUYS ABOUT MY
STRATEGY AND MAYBE CONVINCE THEM
THAT I'M REALLY GOOD AT THIS
GAME
AND I CAN HELP THEM IN THIS
GAME.
THE PLAN IS SET IN MOTION.
I'LL VOTE NAONKA, FLUSH THE
IDOL.
SHE'LL HEAR IT, SHE'LL KNOW IT.
BUT YOU CAN'T LET THAT LEAK,
FABIO, AT ALL.
IT HAS TO BE NAONKA ALL THE WAY.
>> I'M GOING TO BE THE ONE
LEADING THAT CHARGE.
>> AND ALL OF US WITH BRENDA
VOTE FOR JANE.
HOPEFULLY THE IDOL IS FLUSHED,
JANE GOES HOME,
IT ISOLATES CHASE, AND THEN YOU
GUYS RUN IT, MAN.
>> MARTY IS A SMART GUY.
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
HE CAME UP WITH A PRETTY SOLID
PLAN.
IF PROPERLY EXECUTED,
IT WILL DEFINITELY RUFFLE A FEW
FEATHERS.
>> SO GLAD WE'RE TOGETHER, MAN.
>> ME, TOO.
>> THE WHOLE THING JUST CLICKED.
>> ME, TOO, BUDDY.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK BRENDA
THINKS OF CHASE?
>> I'M GUESSED BRENDA IS JUST
KEEPING HER OPTION OPEN.
>> HE'S A BAD HORSE TO RIDE.
>> I BET HE'S IN A BAD MOOD AT
CAMP
AND BRENDA DOESN'T LIKE THAT,
MAN.
WHEN PEOPLE PANIC AND START TO
WORRY--
>> THAT'S WHY I FIND IT HARD TO
BELIEVE SHE WOULD THROW
HER LOT IN WITH THOSE KOOKY
PEOPLE.
>> SASH YOU HAVE TO REASSURE
BRENDA WE WANT HER IN THE GAME.
SHE TRUSTS YOU 100%.
>> I KNOW SHE TRUSTS ME 100%.
I TRUST HER 95%.
THE PLAN MARTY PUT FORWARD MAKES
PERFECT SENSE
BUT I BELIEVE BRENDA AND I ARE
THE TWO BRIGHTEST MINDS OUT HERE
AND IN THE END SHE AND I HAVE
THE POWER
TO SEND WHOEVER WE WANT HOME.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE WITH US.
>> WE DID OUR BEST.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY ONE
THING--
CHASE SHOWED HIS CHARACTER TODAY
BY BELIEVING IN US.
>> YEAH.
>> MARTY, YOU ALL KNOW HOW I
FEEL ABOUT HIM.
SASH IS THE ONLY ONE I TRUST
OVER THERE SO...
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE'RE GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> CHASE, I DON'T THINK HE MADE
A SMART MOVE.
HE SHOULD HAVE CHOSEN THE GUYS.
HE JUST WENT WITH HIS LITTLE
EMOTIONS,
AND HE DIDN'T WANT TO DISAPPOINT
NORTH CAROLINA, JANE, AND MOMMY
FIGURE HOLLY, AND MAYBE ME.
SO HE WENT WITH THE GIRLS.
CHASE DOESN'T MAKE SMART MOVES.
THAT'S HIS PROBLEM.
>> ISN'T THAT CRAZY?
THE ALLIANCE PICKED THE SAME
ROCKS.
>> AND I THINK TOMORROW WE'RE
ALL IN AGREEMENT
ABOUT ONE THING-- AS LONG AS
MARTY IS NOT WINNING
IMMUNITY TOMORROW, HE'S GOING
HOME.
>> I REALLY WANT MARTY OUT OF
HERE.
>> TODAY WAS A HUGE REWARD.
IT DROVE ME CRAZY.
I MEAN-- THAT I MISSED THAT.
BUT I WENT WITH MY GUT, AND I
WANTED TO SHOW THE GIRLS
THEY CAN TRUST ME, AND HOPEFULLY
THAT WILL GET ME
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> DAN AND MARTY ARE REALLY,
REALLY TIGHT.
>> I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW TIGHT
THEY WERE.
>> SEE, AND YOU KNOW AFTER
TODAY,
I'M SURE THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO
GET SASH AND BRENDA.
>> YEAH, BUT I'M NOT GOING TO
SIT THERE AND DOUBT BRENDA
BECAUSE THAT WILL GET HER MAD
AND WE DON'T WANT HER MAD.
HOPEFULLY BRENDA'S IN.
>> GOTTA TRUST HER.
THAT'S ALL YOU CAN DO.
>> BRENDA.
DO YOU THINK WE CAN?
YEAH.
>> I MEAN, IT COMES DOWN TO THE
NEXT-- NEXT VOTE, AND BRENDA
AND SASH ARE IN, WE GET MARTY
OUT, AND WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU REALLY THINK WE CAN TRUST
BRENDA.
>> YEAH.
>> I DO.
>> I MEAN, WE MADE IT THIS FAR
WITH HER.
>> YEAH.
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH BRENDA HAS
DEFINITELY CHANGED.
I'M NOT SURE ABOUT BRENDA.
I'M NOT SURE WHERE HER HEAD'S AT
RIGHT NOW.
WE'VE BEEN AWAY FROM EACH OTHER
SINCE WE DID THE TRIBAL SWAP.
WE DON'T TALK MUCH ANYMORE.
WE TALKED WHEN WE WERE AT THE LA
FLOR CAMP
BUT WE DON'T TALK MUCH.
THAT COULD BE BECAUSE SHE'S
REALLY WITH MARTY.
YOU DON'T GOT TO WORRY
ABOUT BRENDA.
>> JUST DON'T GET ON HER NERVES.
>> YOU SEEM REALLY UNSURE RIGHT
NOW.
ARE YOU JUST THINKING?
>> JUST THINKING.
YOU KNOW, ABOUT SASH.
>> I'D LOVE MARTY OUT FIRST.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU SEEM REALLY UNSURE.
>> NO.
>> YOU KNOW YOU CAN TRUST ME.
YOU'VE KNOWN YOU CAN TRUST ME
FROM THE BEGINNING.
>> CHASE IS A WORRYWART.
"WHAT'S GOING ON, BRENDA?
ARE YOU OKAY?
ARE YOU UNSURE?
YOU SEEM UNSURE?
I'M FREAKING OUT, I'M WORRIED."
YOU KNOW, CHASE IS LIKE A LITTLE
BABY
THAT'S ALWAYS GOING WAH, WAH.
>> YOU SEEM REALLY UNSURE RIGHT
NOW ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> I DON'T REALLY LOOK INTO THE
FUTURE THAT MUCH.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS I CAN'T
STAND IS PARANOIA,
AND CHASE IS TOO PARANOID.
YOU COULD BE TALL AND YOU COULD
BE MUSCULAR,
BUT, REALLY, WHERE'S ALL THE
ALPHA MALE POWER CONTROL?
IT'S AN ILLUSION.
I DON'T NEED TO RUN AROUND
PROVING MYSELF TO ANYBODY.
>> BUT I TOLD THEM DON'T GO OVER
THERE IRKING BRENDA, FOR REAL.
AND WHAT DID HE DO?
CAME OVER HERE AND STARTING
IRKING BRENDA.
WE MAY HAVE TO SWAP YOU OUT FOR
SOMEBODY ON THE OTHER SIDE
BECAUSE YOUR PARANOIA IS GETTING
TO BE TOO MUCH.
>> TREE MAIL!
>> WHOO!
>> READ IT TO US.
>> "THIS NEXT CHALLENGE IS A
TEST OF STRENGTH.
THAT IS, YOUR MEMORY BETTER BE
STRONG.
KNOW WHAT CAME FIRST AND WHAT
CAME LAST
OR BE THE NEXT TO SAY SO LONG."
>> OH, MAN.
IMMUNITY.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY IMMUNITY.
>> TREE MAIL SHOWED UP, SO I'M
HOPING
THE GODS UP THERE THAT WE PRAY
TO KEEP THE GOOD IN
AND TRIUMPH OVER THE EVIL.
THERE'S ONLY ONE REALLY
SERIOUSLY EVIL, DIABOLICAL
PERSON IN THIS GAME RIGHT NOW,
AND THAT'S MARTY.
IF HE DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY, FAT
LADY'S GOING TO BE SINGING.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
AND I'M GOING TO BE THE FAT
WOMAN, ALTHOUGH I'M NOT FAT.
THERE'S A BIG OLD TARGET ON MY
BACK RIGHT NOW
AFTER MARTY'S SLANDEROUS
OUTBURST THE OTHER NIGHT.
SO ANYBODY NEEDS TO WIN, EXCEPT
FOR MARTY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
I WILL TAKE BACK
THE TWO IMMUNITY NECKLACES,
FABIO AND JANE.
THANK YOU, SIR.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
ONLY ONE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE TODAY.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
WE'RE GOING TO TEST YOUR MEMORY.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
A SERIES OF SYMBOLS.
YOU'RE GOING TO USE YOUR CUBE TO
REPEAT THEM BACK TO ME.
YOU GET IT RIGHT,
YOU MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING
WINS IMMUNITY
AND IS GUARANTEED A ONE-IN-10
SHOT AT THE MILLION DOLLARS.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEONE'S RUN AT THE MONEY
WILL COME TO AN END.
ALL RIGHT, YOU READY TO BEGIN?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST ROUND,
FIRST SYMBOL.
SHIP.
MUSKET.
ANCHOR.
SHIP'S WHEEL.
MUSKET.
SHIP.
ALL RIGHT, SHOW ME
THE FIRST SYMBOL.
FIRST SYMBOL, EVERYBODY HAS
SHIP, EVERYBODY WAS CORRECT.
IT WAS A SHIP.
NEXT SYMBOL.
THE SECOND SYMBOL WAS A MUSKET.
EVERYBODY GOT IT RIGHT.
THIRD SYMBOL.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE JANE AND
NAONKA BOTH SAY SHIP'S WHEEL.
EVERYBODY ELSE HAS ANCHOR.
CORRECT SYMBOL WAS ANCHOR.
JANE, YOU'RE OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
NAONKA, YOU'RE OUT
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
AND WITH THAT,
WE LOSE OUR FIRST TWO.
NEXT SYMBOL.
EVERYBODY HAS SHIP'S WHEEL
EXCEPT DAN.
DAN HAS COINS.
CORRECT ANSWER IS SHIP'S WHEEL.
DAN, YOU'RE OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
NEXT SYMBOL.
HOLLY, KELLY, AND SASH
ALL SAY SHIP.
MARTY, BENRY, FABIO, BRENDA,
AND CHASE SAY MUSKET.
CORRECT ANSWER IS MUSKET.
HOLLY'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
PURPLE KELLY IS
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
SASH, OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT, NEXT SYMBOL.
EVERYBODY SAYS SHIP.
EVERYBODY GOT IT RIGHT.
AND WE'RE DOWN TO FIVE.
WE MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
MUSKET.
SHIP.
COINS.
ANCHOR.
DAGGER.
MUSKET.
SHIP'S WHEEL.
HERE WE GO.
SHOW ME THE FIRST SYMBOL.
EVERYBODY SAYS MUSKET.
EVERYBODY IS RIGHT.
NEXT SYMBOL.
EVERYBODY SAYS SHIP, EXCEPT FOR
FABIO, WHO SAYS ANCHOR.
CORRECT ANSWER WAS SHIP.
FABIO'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
NEXT SYMBOL.
EVERYBODY SAYS COINS
EXCEPT FOR CHASE.
CHASE SAYS MUSKET.
HOLD ON, BROTHER.
YOU DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE RIGHT.
CHASE, YOU'RE WRONG.
CORRECT ANSWER WAS COINS.
CHASE IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO MARTY,
BENRY, AND BRENDA.
NEXT SYMBOL.
MARTY AND BRENDA
BOTH SAY ANCHOR.
BENRY SAYS DAGGER.
THE SYMBOL WAS ANCHOR.
BENRY, YOU'RE OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE HAVE OUR FINAL TWO.
MARTY AND BRENDA.
FOR IMMUNITY.
HAVE NOT BEEN THE BEST OF
FRIENDS IN THIS GAME SO FAR.
>> NOT TRUE.
>> Jeff: I'M JUST
SAYING WHAT I SEE.
NEXT SYMBOL.
MARTY AND BRENDA
BOTH SAY DAGGER.
YOU ARE BOTH RIGHT.
NEXT SYMBOL.
>> BRENDA GOT IT.
BRENDA GOT IT.
>> Jeff: MARTY SHOWS THE SHIP'S
WHEEL, BRENDA SHOWS MUSKET.
AND YOU'RE SMILING.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE RIGHT.
MARTY'S WRONG.
BRENDA WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: BRENDA IS SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S VOTE,
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME.
SHOULD BE AN INTERESTING
AFTERNOON.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
HEAD ON BACK TO CAMP.
>> TOSS A BUNCH DOWN.
>> HOO, HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO!
THINK THAT PLAN'S GONNA WORK?
>> NAONKA, AND THEN BLINDSIDING
JANE?
I THINK THE SOONER WE CAN GET
RID OF HER THE BETTER.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M TRYING TO WIN A MILLION
DOLLARS, YOU KNOW.
>> WE GOT TO MAKE SURE NAONKA
FLUSHES THAT IDOL TONIGHT.
WE GOTTA, LIKE,
LET IT LEAK THAT SHE'S...
THAT WE WERE...
>> YOU AND I SHOULD JUST LAY LOW
AND SAY WE'RE VOTING NAONKA...
AND PLAY STUPID.
>> I KNOW, DUDE.
I HATE PLAYING STUPID SO MUCH,
BUT IT'S, LIKE, THE SMARTEST
THING TO DO RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH, IT'S EASY.
>> IT'S REAL EASY.
THAT'S THE GREATEST THING ABOUT
THIS PLAN.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
TO DO A WHOLE LOT,
AND THAT'S A BIG PART
OF THIS GAME, IS LAYING LOW.
YOU KNOW, I CALL IT BEING COOL.
WHATEVER.
JUST NOT TICKING PEOPLE OFF,
AND, YOU KNOW,
IT'S A GOOD STRATEGY
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU KNOW?
>> WHO DO YOU ALL THINK?
>> I THINK GO WITH YOUR HEAD,
NOT YOUR HEART.
>> I'M JUST GOING WITH YOU ALL.
>> I THINK IT'S GONNA BE NAONKA.
I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM EVERYBODY,
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE THAT'S GONNA
BE THE CONSENSUS.
LET ME PUT IT TO YOU THIS WAY,
MAN.
IF SOMEBODY WALKED
INTO YOUR COACH'S OFFICE,
STOLE THE PLAYBOOK,
WENT INTO YOUR LOCKER ROOM,
STOLE EVERY WALLET OUT OF YOUR
PLAYERS AND THEY GAVE IT
TO THE OTHER TEAM AND THEN LIED
TO YOU GUYS,
IS THAT A PLAYER THAT YOU WOULD
WANT TO PLAY NEXT TO?
IS THAT A LINEBACKER YOU WOULD
>> NO.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> I'LL DO IT.
>> I'M ALWAYS WORRIED
WHEN I GO TO TRIBAL.
I KNOW THAT THE OTHER ALLIANCES
ARE GONNA GO FOR ME
BECAUSE I TOOK THE FLOWER.
BUT I'M STRAIGHT
FROM SOUTH CENTRAL L.A.
I HAVE SOME STREET SMARTS AND
I ALWAYS FOLLOW MY INTUITION.
BUT KEEP IN MIND THAT I DO HAVE
AN IMMUNITY IDOL,
AND IF I HAVE TO USE IT FOR
MYSELF TO SAVE MYSELF, I WILL.
>> HE SAID THEY'RE VOTING
NAONKA.
I THINK THEIR PLAN IS TO VOTE
NAONKA
AND THEN ACTUALLY
BLINDSIDE JANE.
>> SO WHO ARE YOU VOTING FOR?
>> I'M VOTING FOR MARTY.
>> HOW ABOUT BRENDA?
>> I HAVEN'T TALKED TO HER.
>> MY TWO CENTS, AND THEN
I WON'T BOTHER YOU AGAIN
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY.
HAS SASH TALKED TO YOU
AT ALL YET?
>> NO, NOT YET.
>> NO? OKAY.
>> WHAT'S THE PLAN?
DID SASHA JUST TELL ME?
>> SASH'S PLAN WAS, YEAH,
HE'LL LAY OUT THE WHOLE THING.
WAS BASICALLY EVERYONE SAY
NAONKA, NAONKA, NAONKA,
FLUSH THE IDOL
AND VOTE JANE OFF.
BLINDSIDE JANE.
THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE...
THAT'S WHAT SASH PROPOSED,
AND EVERYONE SEEMS
TO BE ON BOARD WITH THAT.
AT LEAST, LIKE, FIVE,
OR WHOEVER
ALL OF US VOTED LAST TIME.
>> OKAY. WHAT MARTY SAID
IS ABSOLUTELY TRUE.
JANE IS A HUGE THREAT,
AND IF ANYBODY'S THINKING OF
GOING WITH HER TO THE FINAL
OR LETTING HER EVEN GET CLOSE IS
A FOOL, 'CAUSE SHE WOULD WIN.
>> I ALWAYS PACK MY BAGS
AS IF I MIGHT GO.
>> I KNOW, ME, TOO.
>> AND I'M NOT GOING TO,
I MEAN, I'M GOING TO TONIGHT.
HOPEFULLY THAT'S NOT THE CASE,
ALL RIGHT?
>> I AGREED TO IT.
WE WENT ALONG WITH THE PLAN, BUT
MARTY IS NOT RUNNING THE CAMP.
SASH AND I ARE RUNNING THE CAMP.
>> DID MARTY FILL YOU IN
ON HIS PLAN?
>> YEAH. WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
>> HUH?
>> WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
>> MY PLAN IS WHATEVER
YOUR PLAN IS.
>> ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
>> I ASSUMED GO AHEAD WITH...
>> TELLING EVERYBODY NAONKA.
>> NAONKA. I THOUGHT ALL
THE WOMEN WANTED MARTY GONE.
>> MARTY GONE. THEY DO.
>> THEY WANT HIM OUT SO BAD,
THAT I FEEL LIKE...
JUST LIKE A THORN IN THEIR SIDE.
>> JUST DON'T...
>> HERE, LET'S CHAT
FOR A SECOND.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE HOW
ALL OF A SUDDEN, YOU KNOW,
JANE AND HOLLY AND CHASE'S
CLIQUE ARE DEMANDING THINGS.
>> RIGHT. YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S A SLIPPERY SLOPE.
>> OKAY, SO IF WE TAKE OUT
MARTY,
I'M FINE WITH WHOEVER, RIGHT.
>> JUST PERSONALLY FOR ME,
I WOULD RATHER THAT MARTY STAY
ONE OR TWO TIMES LONGER AT LEAST
BECAUSE I THINK
HE'S A GOOD COOK.
>> RIGHT.
>> I KNOW, HE TELLS ME
EVERYTHING.
>> AND HE TELLS US EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH. SO, IDEALLY, LIKE,
JUST FROM A PERSONAL STANDPOINT,
I WOULDN'T WANT MARTY
TO GO HOME TONIGHT.
>> ME, NEITHER.
>> SASH AND I ARE KIND OF
LIKE THE SWING VOTE.
THE MARTY CREW THINKS WE'RE WITH
THEM TO BLINDSIDE JANE
AND HAVE NAONKA FLUSH OUT
HER IDOL.
AND THEN THE JANE-CHASE CREW
THINKS WE'RE WITH THEM
TO VOTE OUT MARTY.
SO TONIGHT IS REALLY GONNA SHOW
WHO WE REALLY ARE WITH.
I LIKE TO BE IN CHARGE, AND I
KIND OF AM IN CHARGE RIGHT NOW.
SO WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
IT'S REALLY WHATEVER SASH
AND I WANT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
ALINA, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
THE REWARD CHALLENGE.
WE ENDED UP WITH THIS RANDOM
SPLIT OF MEN VERSUS WOMEN.
JANE, YOU GUYS
WERE HEAVILY OUTMATCHED
IN TERMS OF PHYSICAL STRENGTH,
AND YET YOU PUT UP
A GREAT EFFORT.
>> THE HARDEST THING WAS WHEN WE
HIT THE BAMBOO,
IT WAS LIKE WE BOUNCED OFF,
AND THEN WHEN
WE HIT THE BRICK WALL,
WE BOUNCED OFF EVEN HARDER.
>> Jeff: SASH, ON THE FLIP SIDE,
THE GUYS WIN,
YOU GET THIS GREAT REWARD.
WAS THERE A LITTLE BONDING TIME
OR WAS IT ALL STRATEGY?
>> THERE WAS A LOT OF BONDING
TIME.
I THINK THE FIVE OF US
NOT ONLY SHOWED OUR DESIRE
TO WORK AS A GROUP AND ALSO GIVE
US A LITTLE TIME AWAY
FROM THE CAMP TO STRATEGIZE AND
DECIDE SOME OF THE NEXT STEPS.
>> Jeff: FABIO, THE DOWNSIDE
OF BEING WITH ALL THE GUYS
OUT ENJOYING THE REWARD IS YOU
GOT FIVE WOMEN BACK AT CAMP
NONE TOO PLEASED ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH, I'M SURE
THAT STRATEGIZING
DEFINITELY HAPPENED,
AND IT WAS THE FIVE GIRLS PLUS
CHASE, SO THAT'S SIX PEOPLE.
I MEAN, THERE'S A LOT
OF DIFFERENT ANGLES HERE.
I WAS JUST STOKED THAT WE WERE
EATING WHILE WE WERE DOING IT.
>> Jeff: MARTY, LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL YOU WERE PRETTY CLEAR
ABOUT JANE IS SOMEBODY YOU NEED
TO WATCH OUT FOR
AND YOU PROBABLY OUGHT
TO GET RID OF.
FELT LIKE YOU MIGHT HAVE PUT
A TARGET ON YOUR BACK.
>> SHE'S AN INCREDIBLE THREAT.
WHICH IS, AGAIN, I'LL SAY IT,
I'M HONEST,
IT'S A COMPLIMENT TO JANE,
AND MAYBE YOU TAKE SOME RISK
IN DOING THAT.
I FEEL FAIRLY COMFORTABLE,
BUT MY BAGS ARE PACKED.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, HOW MUCH TIME
DID YOU SPEND THINKING ABOUT
WHAT MARTY SAID ABOUT JANE?
>> YOU CAN'T LIE AGAINST THAT
AND SAY SHE'S NOT A THREAT.
IT'S TRUE.
I MEAN, TAKE SOMEONE
LIKE NAONKA
WHO'S, LIKE, "TROUBLEMAKER,"
OR TAKE SOMEONE LIKE JANE
WHO KEEPS FEEDING US FISH,
WHO WOULD YOU LIKE
TO TAKE TO THE END?
I THINK IT'S A NO-BRAINER,
DEPENDING ON HOW
YOU PLAY THE GAME.
>> Jeff: SO, JANE,
YOU ARE A LIKABLE PERSON,
AND IN SOME GAME
THAT WOULD BE REWARDED.
SOMETIMES IN SURVIVOR,
YOU GET PENALIZED.
>> WELL, YOU ALWAYS HAVE
A TARGET ON YOUR BACK.
ME AND MARTY GOT OFF
TO A BAD START.
I STEPPED ON HIS TOES,
HE STEPPED ON MINE.
I PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE KEPT
MY MOUTH SHUT.
SO I THINK I HAVE A TARGET
ON MY BACK, YEAH.
>> Jeff: NAONKA, AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL WE TALKED ABOUT
THE FACT THAT YOU HAD AN IDEA
TO STEAL SOME OF THE FOOD
FROM THE MERGE FEAST.
WHY ARE YOU RUBBING YOUR HEAD
ALREADY?
>> I DON'T, JEFF. GO AHEAD.
>> Jeff: IT CAME UP AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, NAONKA.
YOU SURVIVED THAT VOTE.
IN FACT, IT DIDN'T SEEM
TO HURT YOU AT ALL.
>> IT'S GONNA BE SOMETHING
THAT'S GONNA ALWAYS BE
TALKED ABOUT
'CAUSE IT WAS STUPID, YOU KNOW?
AND I'M HERE.
I'M HAPPY TO BE HERE.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT
ANYMORE, JEFF,
BUT I KNOW
IT'S GONNA BE BROUGHT UP.
>> IT HAS NOT SIT WELL.
THE WAY IT WAS DEALT WITH
AT THE LAST TRIBAL
WAS AS IF IT WAS TRIVIAL.
TO LIE AND TO TAKE FOOD--
THERE IS NO BIGGER SIN.
I MEAN, I KNOW
THERE WERE PRIORITIES HERE
AND SOME OF US HAD
TO GO WITH THE FLOW,
BUT ABSOLUTELY NOT TRIVIAL,
NOT IN ANY WAY.
>> JEFF, I'M NOT PERFECT.
I'M A HUMANITARIAN.
I'M A HUMAN. I SCREW UP.
MARTY SCREWS UP, TOO.
BUT I DON'T LIKE HIM,
HE DON'T LIKE ME.
SO IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE MAD AT MARTY
'CAUSE HE STRATEGIZES?
>> I DON'T LIKE HIM!
I JUST DON'T.
HIS HAIR, HIS WALK SUCKS.
YOU KNOW,
I CAN SEE THROUGH MARTY.
>> LIKE MARTY SAID, WE...
>> FABIO, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T HATE
ON HIS GAME,
BUT I'M COMPETING AGAINST MARTY.
PUT IT IN TERMS
OF A TRACK MEET:
HE'S IN LANE 5
AND I'M IN LANE 4.
I'M GONNA TRY TO GO A LITTLE
FASTER, BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
BEFORE I GO, YOU KNOW, I'M GONNA
TRY TO GIVE MYSELF FIGHT.
I'm GONNA TRY TO JUST
WHOO-WHOO-WHOO, YOU KNOW?
TRY TO SCARE HIM A LITTLE BIT,
YOU KNOW?
'CAUSE THAT'S JUST WHAT YOU DO.
>> I DON'T FOLLOW THAT,
BUT, WHATEVER.
>> Jeff: IS IT WORKING, MARTY?
>> NO. I MEAN, THIS GAME IS
ABOUT INSTINCTS,
AND I HAD A GUT INSTINCT
THAT SAID
THAT'S WHAT THIS PERSON
IS ALL ABOUT.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> AND GUESS WHAT?
SHE IS A LIAR AND A CHEAT
AND A STEAL.
>> WELL, MY DADDY IS IN
INGLEWOOD, CALIFORNIA,
AND I DON'T HAVE NOTHING
TO PROVE TO MARTY.
>> HE'S NOT GONNA BE PROUD
OF YOU, SISTER.
>> OH, HE IS BECAUSE I'M HERE
AND YOU PROBABLY WON'T BE.
(LIGHT LAUGHTER)
>> Jeff: FABIO, YOU LOVE THIS.
>> IT'S CRAZY. LIKE, EVERYTHING
SHE JUST TALKED ABOUT
DOESN'T REALLY MAKE SENSE TO ME.
>> I WANT YOU GUYS
TO KNOW I'M NOT DUMB.
YOU KNOW, I MADE A STUPID MOVE,
BUT I'M VERY FAR FROM STUPID,
OKAY?
>> AND BY THE WAY,
JUST SAYING YOU'RE SORRY,
YOU STILL DID IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> OKAY, WELL, IT'S DONE.
>> OKAY, THEN NOTHING ELSE NEEDS
TO BE SAID ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE PROVING OUR POINT.
>> OKAY, YOU GUYS KEEP TALKING
ABOUT THE DAMN FLOUR.
WHAT THE ... WOULD YOU WANT
ME TO DO?
YOU GUYS CAN BASH ON ME
ALL YOU WANT.
I'M NOT GONNA LOSE ANY SLEEP
BECAUSE I DAMN SURE
DON'T GET SLEEP AS IT.
>> YOU MIGHT TONIGHT.
>> AND YOU MIGHT, TOO, MARTY.
>> ALWAYS A POSSIBILITY.
>> BOTH: MM-HMM.
>> THIS IS CRAZY!
>> THEY THINK THAT THEY'RE
INTIMIDATING ME RIGHT NOW,
AND THEY'RE NOT.
>> WELL, SOMETHING'S GETTING
UNDER YOUR SKIN,
'CAUSE YOU'RE GOING OFF.
>> I LOVE TALKING.
I GO OFF ON YOU ALL THE TIME.
THIS IS NOT GONNA CHANGE
WHO I AM.
BUT IT'S KIND OF FUNNY TO ME
THAT I'M GETTING POUNDED ON
RIGHT NOW.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS GONNA HAPPEN.
THE GUYS BONDED.
I KNOW THEY TALKED SO MUCH ...
ABOUT ME YESTERDAY.
I JUST KNOW. BUT DO I CARE?
>> DOES IT OCCUR TO YOU
THAT PEOPLE ARE SAYING THE SAME
THING ABOUT YOU?
THEY'RE GETTING SICK OF THIS.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE YOU CARE
MORE THAN I CARE.
>> WELL, IT'S IRRITATING ME.
>> WELL, IT IRRITATES THE ...
OUT OF ME, TOO.
THIS IS JUST WHO I AM.
SO WHOEVER DON'T LIKE IT,
'CAUSE I AM ME.
(MARTY CHUCKLES)
... YOU, TOO.
(LAUGHTER)
>> Jeff: OKAY, I GOTTA SAY,
I'M-I'M...
GOD, NAONKA...
I THINK I'M SPEECHLESS
THAT YOU CAN GO OFF
LIKE THIS, TRIBAL AFTER TRIBAL,
AND STILL BE IN THIS GAME.
TELLS ME I SHOULD BE LOOKING
FOR YOU
TO BE SITTING HERE AT THE FINAL.
>> SOMEBODY WANTS TO TAKE ME
BECAUSE I'M BEING A BITCH,
OR I'M JUST EMBARRASSING MYSELF,
IF YOU WILL.
WELL, THEN, SO BE IT.
BUT I'M NOT PUTTING ON A SHOW.
THIS IS WHO I AM.
THIS IS WHAT I'VE BEEN
FOR 27 YEARS.
SO IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
THEN YOU DON'T LIKE IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO GET TO THE VOTE.
BRENDA, YOU HAVE
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
I ASSUME YOU'RE KEEPING IT.
CANNOT VOTE FOR BRENDA.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DAN, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU ARE A DISGRACE TO EVERY
MAN WHO CALLS HIMSELF A FATHER.
THERE'S NO WAY IN HECK I WOULD
ALLOW MY CHILD OR MY GRANDCHILD
TO COME PLAY WITH YOUR CHILDREN,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
>> Y'ALL'S CATFISHING TRIP
HAS BEEN TERMINATED,
'CAUSE Y'ALL MESSED
WITH THE WRONG GATOR, MISSY.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JANE.
MARTY.
JANE.
JANE. THAT'S THREE VOTES JANE.
FOUR VOTES JANE, ONE VOTE MARTY.
MARTY. TWO VOTES MARTY.
MARTY.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JANE,
THREE VOTES MARTY.
MARTY. WE'RE TIED.
FOUR VOTES JANE,
FOUR VOTES MARTY.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES MARTY.
FOUR VOTES JANE.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT
AND THE SECOND MEMBER
OF OUR JURY, MARTY.
THAT'S SIX. THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
MARTY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: WELL,
BASED ON THE VOTE,
IT'S CLEAR YOU ARE NO LONGER
MAKING DECISIONS AS A GROUP,
AND THIS IS WHERE IT GETS
REALLY INTERESTING
AND VERY COMPLICATED.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR:
>> OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS UN-FREAKING-BELIEVABLE.
>> WORDS CAN'T EXPLAIN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS.
I'M GONNA CRY.
>> I AM... OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THIS IS A DAY FROM HELL.
>> I WOULDN'T CHANGE A THING
I DID TO MY GAME.
THERE'S ALWAYS GONNA BE A RISK,
AND IT CAUGHT ME TONIGHT.
IT'S ALWAYS FRUSTRATING TO LOSE,
BUT I WAS NOT FRUSTRATED
BY ANYTHING OTHER THAN
THERE WEREN'T ENOUGH PEOPLE
REALLY PLAYING THE GAME,
BUT OBVIOUSLY THERE WERE ENOUGH
PLAYING THE GAME TONIGHT.
I DIDN'T SEE IT COMING.
OTHERWISE, I WOULDN'T BE SITTING
HERE RIGHT NOW.
IT SUCKS NOT TO BE IN THE GAME,
ABSOLUTELY SUCKS.