This season's castaways have endured 27
days on the rugged shores of Nicaragua.
They have battled exhaustion,
starvation, and each other.
I'll push you so hard that
damn leg will fly off.
In their fight to become
the sole survivor.
If you are 40 and older,
you're over here.
30 and younger, you're over here.
For the first time in "survivor"
history, tribes were
divided strictly by age.
The young guns.
I'm young at heart!
Pitting young against old in an
epic struggle for dominance.
On the la flor twrieb players
weren't afraid to use their
youth to their advantage.
I have always used flirting and
I will use that if I have to.
I trust our five and that is it.
Drawing clear lines within the tribe.
The older tribe had wisdom and
experience but not even the
presence of super bowl winning coach
jimmie Johnson... team huddle.
...Could keep some of the tribe
from going over the edge.
She stole my shoes.
She stole them.
It's a good thing you're not a guy.
It's enjoyable just to watch a
little bit of tension in this tribe.
Marty finally took control at espada.
Do not mess around with me.
I mean, I'm playing
this game for real.
But they could only watch
as young tribe won early
and often, slashing the older
tribe's numbers and putting them
in serious jeopardy, having only
been to tribal council once, the
younger tribe seemed invincible.
Drop your buffs.
But a surprise switch changed
the game dramatically.
At the new espada, older members
holly and Dan joined forces with
their new tribemates to
vote out two of their own.
Brenda and sash reined over the
new la flor, leaving the espada
puppet master Marty stripped
of his power and his idol.
Going into the merge, the
younger members had the numbers
and Brenda and sash
still called the shots.
Marty, is not running the camp.
Sash and I are running the camp.
100%.
But as new alliances formed,
serious cracks begin to
show in the old la flor core alliance.
20 castaways set out
on this epic journey.
Only nine remain.
Tonight, in a special episode
of "survivor," we take a deeper
look at how the final nine have survived
27 days of grueling competition.
New scenes reveal the conflicts,
strategies, and power plays that
have brought these nine within days
of becoming the sole survivor.
The older espada tribe
arrived at camp on kay one.
We did it, guys.
How are you?
Ready to put their wisdom
and experience to work.
I'll be interested to see how
our older people hold up.
We're the underdog, the older
folks, but I hope we come
together enough to where
we can surprise people.
Shelter is the most
important thing right now.
Marty's right, shelter first.
We need to figure out where
we're going to do it, though.
There's low tide right now.
You tonight want to be too close
to the water see, I think...
As soon as we hit the beach,
everybody startsiacking, yelling.
Everybody is excited.
We had all chiefs and no Indians.
Can I say one thing?
There are some palm fronds.
I think we collectively agreed... there's
a lot of testosterone over there.
Tyrone wants to go in control.
If the shelter is here...
Jimmie Johnson is used to
being in a control situation.
If somebody wants to try and see what
it's like to split a bamboo in half...
Marty looks like he wants to be a
little bit of a leader, t too.
So let them lead, you know, but give me
a couple of good ideas once in a while.
We need to figure out about how
high we're going to have it.
The power struggle has began, man.
The game is on.
People want to act like they know
what they're doing, build a shelter.
Joe pesci over there I think knows
a little bit about construction.
Who the hell ever built
a shelter before.
I was born and raised
in Brooklyn, New York.
They think I haven't built a shelter?
We can't just sleep on that.
Five hours of daylight left.
Okay.
I'm all for... Watch it!
Watch it.
I don't see progress.
But I do hear conversation.
And it's a bit entertaining.
We may end up keeping this roof.
Jimmy t.
'S style is, "look at me!
I crave attention."
Listen.
I don't feed into that.
Because it's just like a crying child.
Necessary their diaper needs to
be changed, if you don't respond
to that nonsense, they'll stop.
I feel like I'm being
ignored by you guys.
We can walk while we talk.
Each guy grab each a pole and we put it
up here and we've got our structure.
I heard some rah-rah going
on, a couple of profanities.
The girls are doing great.
We're weaving palm frondz.
The boys have built and unbuilt the
shelter our or five times already.
I think it's going to
be a long night for us.
All right, that was good.
Are we done?
Time to go home?
Things were much more relaxed
at the young la flor tribe?
Time to swim?
Where fun was priority number one.
Ready, one, two, three.
Okay.
So it was like, hi, my name is Brenda.
I'm getting to my underwear now.
As the younger tribe we have a huge
advantage because we have so much energy.
All of us are fit.
And we're all so happy to be here.
Underwear!
Whooo!
Those are cute!
I think the biggest advantage
is we're getting along so well.
We're in Nicaragua.
I am really happy that I'm
on the younger tribe.
We're not really set in our ways.
Like older people, they're kind of like...
They're already set in their ways.
They think they know everything
and it's going to be a lot
harder for them to bond and click.
The la flor tribe just
wants to be in the water.
I'm with a bunch of idiots.
I wish that I had been on the other
tribe because they're a lot smatter.
I believe they had a shelter.
I believe they had a door.
Probably a few windows and
basement and attic because I
know those women were sitting up
there weaving, weaving, we'ving.
I know it.
They do have wisdom.
I'm with young idiots.
It's ridiculous.
Hey, do you need another vi vine?
Maybe eventually.
By nightfall at espada, the tribe had
built some camaraderie, along with some
should the.
I'll put my hand through the top and
you hit the target other all right.
Throw one up here.
Hold on, hold on.
Thank you, doctor.
I got a little upset
with some guys earlier.
There's a bunch right here.
Maybe they weren't eloquent
in the way they spoke to me.
But guess what?
I like the way guys are
starting to step up.
I think we're starting
to unite as a team.
I think that's important.
It can't get any better than this.
One, two, three espada!
I'm about ready to turn in.
Good night!
The game plan is to try
to get some sleep.
We od our asses off tonight.
Everybody worked hard today.
You all right?
Yeah.
We have a ramshackle shelter
there but at least it's
something we can all huddle
under and try to get a few
hours' rest and make this place
a lot more livable tomorrow.
What a day today was, seriously.
So far, so good, man.
, you know, you just gotta be careful.
This game changes all tomb.
It's never what you
think it's going to be.
Oh!
So I get to spoon with Danny tonight?
That sounds so wrong.
Stew time.
Fabio needs a bubble wrapped
all around his body.
By day four at espada, clear roles
were established among the tribe.
While we've got everybody here maybe
we should have a conversation.
With jimmie Johnson emerging
as the group's natural leader.
First of all, sleeping arrangements,
we've got to readjust.
Jimmy, he didn't even
have a spot last night.
We have to come up with a plan.
We have to have a plan of rotation.
Tonight I'll sleep on that backside.
So I get to spoon with Danny tonight?
Oh, no you spoon... I spooned
with Tyrone last night.
You've spooned with about everybody.
That sounds so wrong.
But you are my best
spoon, I promise you.
I don't know about you, but I
needed a cigarette when I woke up.
No wonder I was up all night.
At la flor, fabio came in with a very
different strategy... avoid leadership at
all costs.
I came out here with a game plan.
I feel like I'm going to be able
to kind of stay under the radar
and slither through things.
I'm just trying to stay cool, stay
confident, but not be stupid.
Did you rub your eye?
Yeah.
Really?
I went and picked hot chili
pepper because our breath was
disgusting this morning, and we
needed something to get rid of it.
Lean your head back.
Oh, my God.
It hurts to open it so bad.
Fabio is hilarious.
He always gets himself
in a sticky situation.
He always gets himself hurt somehow.
I touched the seeds and everything.
Will this go away or what?
I think fabio needs a bubble
wrapped all around his body
because no matter what he does to
himself, he's going to get an owe.
He's stupid.
He's an idiot.
I have to wash my hands
before I touch anything else.
Imagine going to the bathroom
touching the chili and this...
I don't know if I'm accident prone.
I mean, things happen out here, yeah.
The yellow are really
hard to pull off.
Can we even eat these?
Careful, there's a
beehive up there, too.
There's a beehive up here?
Do you see it?
There were all the ants inside of it.
Maybe that's called
accident prone, whatever.
Hey, guys.
Ow!
Thorns, man.
I don't think people are really
going to see me as I threat.
They're going to be, well, he's
young, he's goofy, and we're not
too worried about him.
Whoa!
Stew time.
Ow.
Yeah, baby.
Doesn't that... doesn't
that happen to everybody?
I mean... not just me, I don't think.
By day nine hunger and
fatigue were already taking
a toll and paranoia set in in espada.
Has anybody made an alliance with you?
No.
Okay, listen.
There's something that's going to
happen tomorrow at the challenge.
That's my guess, okay.
I think what's going to happen
is a lot of the city kids, okay,
are going to merge over to this
tribe, or they're going to put
us with the city kids and the country
kids are going to come over here.
That's why nobody is making alliances.
Something is going to happen
tomorrow at the challenge.
Holly I think is a very nice person,
but she's... she's off the deep end.
When you hear her talk, you
can hear the nervousness.
You can see the tension in her eyes.
She feels the same stress they feel.
She needs to do well in this
game and she's not, and now he's
hitting the panic buttons.
I'm worried that you're over-thinking it
and just... right now you still seem a
little edgy.
No, that's because how I am.
I think about things.
But it's going to...
it's eating at you.
The strategy part, I am not going to lie,
I struggle with the strategy part.
What's her name?
Oh, God.
I'm terrible at names.
And that's one thing I didn't think I
would struggle with coming into the game.
I thought I maybe over-analyzed
it even before I started but
hopefully it won't get me at the end.
So don't worry... I appreciate you
coming and sharing it with me.
It sounds like it's a possibility.
I think it's a very...
pretty strong possibility.
Okay.
Things weren't much better
at la flor, where severe
weather conditions tested the
resolve of the entire tribe.
I hope this rain stops, man.
It sucks so bad, man.
I'm just so frustrated.
It's the rain and just
being, like, wet and cold.
I haven't really been, like, warm.
Like every night has been freezing.
Everyone else is putting up with it.
I don't understand where
why it's so hard for me.
If I want to go home, if I just
want it to be over, they're
going to think... they're just going
to think I'm, like, super awakweak.
It's killing me out here.
I want to quit.
If you can go through this,
you can go through anything.
This rain is hideous.
It can break you down and it
reveals your true character.
Just like a game, it's 10%
physical and 90% mental.
So if I have to be that girl's rock to
keep her protected then I'll do that.
Purpleicle Sean important
number for our alliance.
And we're going to carry
her as far as we can.
Wow.
The river' river's into the oce.
We had quite the rainstorm but
we're in the middle of the
rainfoster, so what did you expect?
Look at this.
This is all about the
crack right here.
Watch this.
Watch this piece.
Oh, my God.
We better step back here.
I feel like this is, like,
some kind of 2012 movie.
Kelly purple is a huge waste of space.
She bitches and moans about
anything and everything.
That's sad to me.
She's definitely involved
with Brenda's alliance and I
think it's time for her to go home.
At espada, jimmie Johnson became the
first casualty of the leadership battle.
Jimmy, the tribe has spoken.
But the war was far from over.
With jimmie Johnson gone, the
remaining men at espada angled
to fill the leadership vacuum.
Actually, we're doing pretty good.
It's a good fire.
I've had a plan since I arrived
and started playing this game
and my game has finally arrived.
As much as you can ever say
anything in this game, and you
can't ever be overly cocky,
but I'm in control finally.
I'm in control of this tribe.
Haerg man, we should move this
fire a little further away.
These flames, all we need is the
wind and can will catch the wood
pile and then it will catch on to the
shelter and then we've got problems.
It's not catching.
Huh?
It's definitely not catching.
You know what?
I'm going to slide this over man.
It won't hurt to slide it over.
I'm not trying to impede on
your situation but I'm just
telling you from
experience I've seen it.
That's kind of what I do for a living?
You hear me?
Yeah, he's a fireman, I get it.
But he felt we were in a danger
zone and too much of the wood I
had nearby was going to catch
fire and blah, blah, blah.
And like, come on, man.
I know what the guy is all about.
He likes to hear himself speaks.
He needs to feel that people are
listening to him as he asserts himself.
If this lights up and then the whole
shelter... do whatever you want with the
fire.
You.
You can be mad if you want but
I'm going to push the fire
away because I'm not sleeping in the
rain any more than I already have.
I think Marty is not used
to taking a back seat.
I think his little... whatever...
his eago or pride got in the way.
He threw a little hissey fit and
stormed off like a little girl.
When I was talking about the
fire and I said we probably need
to move it over and you said,
"don't the thing all up."
I'm just saying.
When you pulled the whole
fire I've been carefully
constructing and everything
else you have to give some
consideration into the time
and effort I put into it.
I'm giving you all that.
But I'm just telling you,
there's a way to talk to me.
I talk with you with with respect
and I felt like you were
disrespectful to me and if you
are disrespectful to me again
it's going to get ugly.
Now you're throwing a real heavy
disrespectful to when all I said was, "don't
with my whole fire."
Come on, man, don't you
think that's exaggerating.
And now you said, "Marty, don't you
ever be disrespectful to me again."
And I don't know what.
Some kind of threat or something.
I don't respond well to that.
Hey, man, don't push me that way.
I'm not going to tolerate being
pushed that way, either.
Don't tell me I'm wrong.
Don't threaten me.
Now you've stepped too far.
We've moved on.
Like men, I thought we had moved on.
Whatever you want to do, but
we're playing the game.
I came to you right now, and I
knew it wasn't going to be an
easy conversation for you or me.
When you threaten somebody,
it usually isn't.
No, if I was threatening
you would know it.
Trust me, game or no game.
I would just love to be able to throw
down tonight and say, "dude, here it is.
Wake up, dude.
Wake up and smell the roses."
Guess who's going to be
the number one target?
Jane, I don't know where
her loyalties will lie.
Beg, borrow, steal,
whatever I've got to do.
I'm going to try to win
a million dollars.
Do you know where Jane is?
I want to work with you
till the end game.
Yup.
I do kind of believe sash right now.
He would be one of the easiest to beat
at the end for a million dollars.
0t
after a surprise tribe switch on day 12,
former espada members were suddenly
outnumbered at the new la flor and had
to scramble to prove their worth.
Where are you two from?
Miami.
Oh, okay.
St. Louis.
My position when I was on
espada was totally solid.
Now coming here, there's five of
them, three of the older tribe.
My position is not so good.
I had fire within 20 minutes of camp.
Wow.
I like you.
You fish, right?
I fish.
Jane, I don't know where
her loyalties will lie.
I think she may be bonding with them.
She's the most skilled
person out here.
I call her "survivor MacGyver."
She can do anything.
He gets fish, she gets crark
she has boundless energy.
And it's hard to argue against a
full belly so I'm very worried
that Jane's ability to bring in
food for the camp is going to be
what sends Marty and I home.
One of my strategies right
there is I'm just trying to be
the provider out here.
Trying to come in this game
as fully prepared as I can.
I mean, I started kind of like
restricting my food a couple of
months ago, just in case I got
on the show so that I wouldn't
feel all the hunger pains.
Not only that, I bought me a
sauna, and I started sitting in
it up to 170 crazy so the
heat doesn't bother me.
I think that paid off.
Hopefully, fingers crossed,
I'll get fish today.
It worked!
Whooo!
I'm starving.
I want me a fish.
I'm gonna eat this one I just caught.
Every now and then, the
provider needs a meal.
Well, just too late in the day,
not enough heat in the sun.
I'm going to go get me a stick
out of the fire and see if I can
sneak it down here.
I was just trying to divert
attention away from the campfire
so it won't look suspicious because
I really want to steal fire embers.
Y'all want to go help
wash all those crabs?
Yeah, I can do that.
Somebody ought to go help her.
She's losing thim.
Some of them jumped out.
Oh, they did.
Run help her.
Everybody upons me knows that
I'm a very honest person.
How I play this game has nothing
at all to do with my real life.
I'm out to win a million dollars.
Beg, bor oh, steal, whatever I
gotta do, I'm gonna try and win
a million dollars.
Do you know where Jane is?
Oh, this is going to be so good.
I got me a meal.
And it's in my stomach, not theirs.
On the new espada tribe, the addition
of four young members forced the older
tribemates to rethink
their strategies.
Who's here from our old
team, our old tribe?
Me, you, Tyrone, and who else?
Yve.
I don't see anybody beating us.
I don't, either.
You picked the cream of the crop.
Thanks, Dan.
It's true.
Brand new game, brand new people.
As far as strategy, I'm probably...
I'm probably super vulnerable here.
I mean, I'm the oldest guy by far.
Whenever I get in front of the
mirror next time I'll be pulling
hair out of my ears and
shaving my beard off.
I think I'm going to let
it go salt and pepper now.
As long as it's not all salt.
It's pretty long.
Yeah, look at his roots.
Let's see your hair.
It looks like a wig.
It does
oh, my God, Dan!
Oh, no way!
Leave it.
I have a major strategy now.
I'm trying to make new friends, yeah.
I'm trying to get in with them
and, you know, I'm trying... I'm
trying to get into the crowd.
I'm a competitive guy.
I don't want to lose it.
The kids like me, you know.
But who knows, I could
be screwed tonight.
They may be playing a game
with me and I'm gone.
Show up at the challenge
like that tomorrow.
Yeah!
Just do it.
It will be so intimidating.
Dan is hilarious, and
he's totally valuable.
He's valuable because he's week.
His position is the number because
& that's why we need him.
He knows that he's weakand he's
happy that we keep him around so
he'll be loyal to us.
There you go.
That's amazing.
We day 16 at the new la
flor, mart I's grip on the
game and his idol were awakened,
while save began a power move to
become the game's new puppet master.
I was just curious to have
you walk me through what the
thinking was so I can understand
what the thinking was.
There's no doubt that you having the idol
makes, you know, some people nervous.
It's absolutely ridiculous for
me to do any kind of move or
try to leverage that idol pre-merge.
At this point in time I'm
not controlling the game.
I'm no longer in the driver's seat.
So I'm along for the expried that's
the best that I can do right now.
I think with everyone here on
la flor, I think you may be one
of the only people that may have a
50-50 shot of winning at the end.
I'm telling you this to try to
tell you what my thoughts are.
I'm not just thinking merge.
I'm thinking also... clearly.
Long term.
Sash is a pretty smart player.
And when he laid out his plans
for me, I was, you know, further
impressed with the way he's
thinking about this game.
But you caint be cocky or
over-confident in this game but
I do believe sash right now.
I want to work with
you to the end game.
Yeah.
I'm all for it, man.
There is a little bit of truth to what I
said to Marty about going to the end.
I think of everyone at la flor
right now, he'd be one of the
easiest to beat at the end
for a million dollars.
If we have each other's backs,
why not go to the end?
I've been making end
agreements with everyone.
I think it would be great if we
watched out for each other's back.
I would think we're top four.
I would love to get all
the way to end with you.
I want to make a safe pact with
every single member of la flor
to guarantee me a final
spot at the end.
I see us moving, you and I
personally, moving much further
along in the game together.
Love to do it, man.
Saying that you want someone
to be next to you at final
tribal council and promising
it are two different things.
Come final tribal council, they'll
number for a rude awakening.
I think we could really
dominate this game.
I think so, too, man.
Whoever did it, something
should happen to them.
To them or their family.
Chase and Jane, they're tight
but I don't think he's smart
enough or bold enough to make a move.
I just hope Brenda ain't
playing y'all for a fool.
On day 19, la flor moved over to the
espada camp and the two tribes became one.
Libertad.
Oh, my God!
Chocolate chip cookies!
Rum!
No.
Yeah!
But the celebration didn't last long.
Old alliances were immediately
tested and new pains were formed
when naonka committed the
ultimate crime... stealing food.
I saw her put the flour in the bag.
And I couldn't understand why.
I should have confronted her
right away and I didn't.
They're so stupid.
Hey, where's the flour?
Naonka, did you put the flour back
in the chest after you used...
everybody saw me put it in there.
You didn't see me then you didn't
see me but I put it in there.
That doesn't just get swept
away by the tide, you guys.
No, I think it's pretty
obvious somebody stole it.
Whoever did it, something
should happen to them.
To them or their family.
They should go home.
This is how I feel.
Yeah.
Stealing food.
When you have a guilty conscience,
you have to say something.
You can't live with it.
So she came to me and she
didn't know what she should do.
Are you going to go
back and say something?
No, what am I going to say?
I just don't want you to.
So how are you going to get
out of this situation?
I'm going it it it it to put it out
there and not say anything else.
You're going to put it in
a pile and not saying.
Nay, as a mom, okay?
Yeah.
The only thing I can tell you
is when you do something wrong,
it's better to confess
and say you're sorry.
You're going to get
way farther in life.
So that's the only
advice I can give you.
Okay?
Okay.
I don't know, something about holly.
She kind of remind me of
my mom, and I respect her.
It helps me out a lot, and I
would like to have holly here
for as long as we could have her here,
until she's not valuable anymore.
Why did you tell me?
Because I love you.
That's why.
And it took a lot more fee to
say that because I'm ed up.
That's okay.
I really up.
I feel really bad.
Go put it back.
Thank you.
It's okay.
We all make mistakes.
My mothering instincts are
definitely kicking in with these
kids, and it kind of helps
because she look as at me as a
mom figure so I definitely
have her on my side.
I'll start it off.
Earlier this morning, after we
made the tortillas, I did put
everything back in there.
I did grap the flour.
And my purpose for grabbing the
flour was to measure it out to
put half and half because we were
using a whole lot of food, okay?
Don't think it's strange to
see a young woman go nuto.
If it happens to a
woman, you expect it.
It's that Brooklyn attitude.
If one of the guys had done that
I would have told him to get the
out of here and don't come bab.
That's for sure.
Let's go get it and bring it here.
You know it was here.
You don't remember?
You don't... well, I just
said I don't remember.
How do you not remember?
I just need a moment so I
can, just, like, look.
Naonka obviously wasn't thinking
straight, you know, and
for her to do something like this.
I just hope she goes home soon.
And that would be fine.
It's so immature.
I am so pissed off at naonka.
She is way too emotional to
have as a core alliance.
It really made me question her
intelligence and really where
her focus is on the game.
She might not be the best
person to go to the end with.
Where's the flour?
Is it at a tree.
There's a tree over here and
there's an arrow going to it and
I've been looking for it.
You don't remember which tree?
No.
There's an arrow on the ground.
I made an arrow with sticks.
I feel like we've been over this area.
This sucks.
You rail screwed up.
You've just got to trust 100%
that our alliance is still strong.
I'm not going to blind side you.
We still need you.
You still need us.
Yeah.
So let's go.
I was just shocked that naonka
would do something so stupid.
Like, you're in a perfect alliance.
You've got everything going for
us and you're going to go put a
target on your back which
hurts our alliance.
Like, come onaonka.
Stop being so stupid.
It could be right here.
Here it is.
Where was it?
It has not been opened
since this morning.
We've got it.
We found it.
Where was it?
Over there.
At that tree.
You really mistaked over
there for right here?
Yes, I did.
We've got to get her out now.
I like her... well, I
don't want to say that.
With naonka's flour scandal
behind them, the tribe
took time away from the game
to let their hair down.
♪ He's always my very best friend
I'm just standing here ♪
Singing a song for me is therapy.
I started writing songs about a
month and a half after my dad died.
I think that was the first time,
you know, I've shared some of my
music with my tribemates.
I'm just trying to be the guy
that everyone likes and try to
get along with everyone.
* He was my hero, dad you were,
larger than life *
Chase's song about his dad
got me super emotional.
Singing, music always has all
these emotions, and I thought no
one could see me, but I started
to tear up a bit just thinking
about... just the whole thing.
Just so many emotions.
That was great.
But I just have to remind myself
to stay focused on the game.
My life will never be
the same, ever again.
Anybody who wants to really play
this game and win this game
has to do so without emotions.
I need to go to bed.
Yeah, me, too.
Chase is super emotional.
He's not thinking about the game.
He's just trying to be nice,
which is great, good for you.
Put that's not going to make you win.
So you go home feeling like a
great guy, but you will go home
without a until dollars and someone
else will, which is fine for me.
By day 27, power couple sash and Brenda
were in complete control of the tribe.
It should really be you
and me running the show.
I know you're working your magic,
just like I am, with all
the guys and everything else.
Exactly.
So I'm not worried about it.
But, you know, not everyone is
as smart as we are, either.
So I know all the guys
like you, you know.
Chase is definitely
on the out with them.
They would much rather
have you on our side.
I'm on whichever side is
more convenient for us.
For us to get to the end.
Brenda and I believe we're the
two smartest people in the game.
Both she and I have almost cast a
special spell over pretty much
everyone in the tribe.
So Brenda and I have the power
to send whoever we want home.
I'm, you know, telling all these
people, "oh, year, final three."
But you're really the only one
I care about going to the end
with, and whoever our third
is... doesn't matter.
Is, whoever, so.
But it can't be chase.
Brenda and I are in the driver's seat.
However, we both understand
that we're probably the biggest
threats for the million
dollars at the end.
So although we're conspiring
together to make it to the end,
I don't know if we both will.
My only concern right
now is chase and Jane.
They're tight.
But I don't think he's smart enough for,
like, or bold enough to make a move.
Brenda and sash's arrogance would prove
to be a serious blind spot in their
strategy purpose they were about to
discover the limits of their employer.
Hey, Jane.
I trust you and I know you trust me.
I don't want to sit here and
vote something against you.
Right now I'm not sure but voting out
Brenda is the right thing to do.
I know brendaments to get me out.
I think.
We can get her out when we
want is the only thing.
Chase and fabio grabbed me, and
they're like, "well, I just
don't think it's a good
idea to vote Brenda out."
And I'm looking at him like sucker!
What have they done to you?
You're a hell of a dude, and I'm
telling you, you've got a great
brain up there.
I'm trying to make in roads with
fabio to open his eyes up that
Brenda is going to
use him like a pawn.
But fabio can't see it.
Chase can't see it because she
has her magic powers over these
young men, and they're falling for it.
I don't think that's the
best thing to do, man.
I really don't?
What do you think?
Who?
Sash.
I don't think they're going
to let you go too close.
See, I like sash.
I think sash is the biggest
threat around here.
Sash don't want to take me
or you to the final three.
He doesn't want to do that.
Because he knows you or I will win.
I would rather her go
sooner than later.
Sash and then her and then, you
know, holly and everybody is
still around, all the nice people.
'Cause we're good.
I just don't want to see evil win.
I feel good that, you know, we
pulled you... side and talked to you.
Okay.
Are you trusting me right now?
Yeah, I trust you.
I mean, I do.
I just hope Brenda ain't
playing y'all for a fool.
I don't want to vote Brenda out.
I don't think she's lied to me.
And it's... it sucks right notice,
but at some point in the
game, you've got to chop the
neck of the person that you
might be closest with, and if
thathat gets me further in the
game, I'm going to have to do it.
At tribal council, chase
broke rank from his old
alliance and sided with
his new ally, Jane.
The black widow Brenda was
voted out in a landed slide.
Brenda, the tribe has spoken.
Only nine castaways are left.
Oh, my God!
The end is in sight.
What!
But the closest they get.
Straight out lied to you and me both.
He talks too much.
He's paranoid.
Strategy intensifies.
Swear on your mom you
will not backstab me.
Conflict escalates.
Who will outwit the
cutthroat competition.
If we stay a strong four we dominate.
Who will out-play in
grueling challenges?
Fabio fighting for the lead.
Who the out-last the
extreme conditions?
I made it this far.
I'm proud of myself.
Who will become the sole survivor?
And then the rest of the
game is smooth sailing.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next week on an
all-new "survivor."
As the storms get stronger.
It's like class-three rapids.
Naonka gets awaker.
As it rains and pours it
makes me feel like crap.
And purple Kelly finally
has something to say.
I don't know how much more
physically I can put up with this.
Fish, fish.
It's the fish dance.
Fish dance.
Sync by YYeTs.net for Addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com