>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY
ON "SURVIVOR."
IN A VAST AND UNFORGIVING
NICARAGUAN RAIN FOREST,
FORMER N.F.L. COACH
JIMMY JOHNSON EMERGED
AS A LEADER OF THE OLDER TRIBE,
BUT MARTY WAS ENVIOUS
OF THE COACH'S STAR POWER.
>> I NEED TO REMOVE HIM
SO PEOPLE WILL LOSE THEIR DADDY
AND THEY'LL HAVE TO COME TO ME.
ON THE YOUNGER TRIBE, BRENDA,
A FORMER N.F.L. CHEERLEADER,
WAS AT THE TOP
OF THE FOOD CHAIN.
>> I HAVE PEOPLE ON MY SIDE
WITHOUT DOING ANYTHING.
I GET A GOOD VIBE FROM NAY
AND I'M TIGHT WITH CHASE.
WE COULD RULE THIS.
KELLY B. AND ALINA WERE
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE FOOD CHAIN,
BUT THEY HAD A CLUE
TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> WE KEEP IT BETWEEN US.
>> AT THE CHALLENGE, THE YOUNGER
TRIBE TOOK A BIG RISK
BY NOT USING THE MEDALLION
OF POWER.
>> WE CAN TAKE THEM
WITHOUT USING IT.
>> Jeff: AND THE RISK PAID OFF.
BECAUSE WHILE JIMMY T.
DISTRACTED THE OLDER TRIBE...
>> YOU'RE WASTING ME BACK HERE.
>> JIMMY T., BE QUIET.
>> Jeff: ...THE YOUNGER TRIBE
CRUISED TO VICTORY.
>> IF THESE PEOPLE KNEW
WHAT THEY WERE DOING
I WOULD BE THE LEADER
OF THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: AFTER THE CHALLENGE,
WITH TOTAL DISREGARD
FOR KELLY B.'S ARTIFICIAL LEG,
NAONKA TACKLED HER
IN ORDER TO GET A NEW CLUE
TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I'LL PUSH YOU SO HARD THE LEG
WILL FALL OFF.
>> Jeff: SHE SHARED THE CLUE
WITH BRENDA.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, JIMMY T.
WAS GUNNING FOR JIMMY J.
>> MAYBE I'M A THREAT
TO HIS LEADERSHIP ROLE
BECAUSE I AM A LEADER
WHERE I COME FROM.
>> Jeff: THE COACH AND DAN
WERE THOUGHT TO BE
THE WEAKEST PLAYERS BUT ONLY
JIMMY WOULD ADMIT TO IT.
>> I'M THE OLDEST PLAYER
AND ONE OF THE WEAKEST, TOO.
>> Jeff: BETWEEN MARTY'S
ALPHA MALE COUP
AND JIMMY JOHNSON'S HONESTY,
THE COACH WAS SENT HOME.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
IN VOTING OUT JIMMY JOHNSON
YOU VOTE OUT A PROVEN LEADER.
WHO'S GOING TO STEP UP
AND FILL THOSE SHOES?
17 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> HOW ABOUT YOU?
YOU GONNA MAKE IT
THROUGH THE NIGHT?
HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN THE GOING GETS TOUGH,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THE LEADERSHIP
THAT JIMMY JOHNSON SUPPLIED
IN EVERYBODY'S EYES WAS NOTHING.
HE GAVE A COUPLE
OF CHEERLEADER SPEECHES
THAT ANY CHUCKLEHEAD COULD DO.
HE DIDN'T PUT
HIS BEST PEOPLE FORWARD.
HE DEFINITELY WASN'T
A JIMMY T. FAN
AND I WASN'T GOING TO GET
A LOT OF PLAYING TIME
WITH HIM CALLING THE SHOTS
AND IF HE WAS A PLAYER
HE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ON MY ALLIANCE, THAT'S FOR SURE.
SO I'M NOT GOING
TO MISS HIM TOO MUCH.
BAD WAVES PASSING ON THE BEACH
AND FOR ONE DESPERATE MOMENT.
HE CAME BACK IN OUR MEMORY,
GUY'S SO CRAZY, SO CLOSE.
AND STILL JUST OUT OF REACH...
>> JIMMY T. IS PUTTING
ON THE JIMMY T. SHOW,
ANNOYING, SINGING,
TRYING TO DO HIS BEST.
IT IS JIMMY T., MAN,
THAT'S WHO THIS GUY IS.
HE'S A LOUD MOUTH, HE JUST...
HE HAS TO HEAR
HIS OWN VOICE 24/7.
TAKE IT EASY, BABY, MAKE IT
LAST NIGHT, LAST ALL NIGHT...
>> IT'S JUST...
THIS GAME TRIES YOUR PATIENCE
IN SO MANY WAYS
AND THAT GUY'S JUST...
IT'S JUST OBNOXIOUS.
SO I MEAN ALL YOU'VE GOT
TO DO WITH JIMMY T.
IS GIVE HIM JUST A LITTLE BIT
OF ROPE.
THAT'S ALL HE NEEDS
AND HE'LL HANG HIMSELF
FROM THE NEAREST BRANCH.
>> WOW, THIS IS
ABSOLUTELY CRAZY.
>> SOMEPLACE ON NICARAGUA
THEY MUST HAVE HAD EIGHT
OR TEN INCHES OF RAIN
AND ALL THAT WATER WE'VE HAD
MIXED WITH THE LAST COUPLE
OF DAYS
OBVIOUSLY IS JUST COME ON DOWN
AND FOUND ITS WAY BACK
TO THE OCEAN.
>> THE ENTIRE BEACH
IS JUST COVERED WITH DEBRIS.
ALL SORTS OF WOOD
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
OUR BEACHFRONT HERE IS GONE.
YOU CAN'T EVEN GET IN THERE.
AND IT'S ALL COVERED WITH MUD.
THE OCEAN'S ALL FILLED WITH MUD.
IT'S REALLY A MESS.
>> IT'S BEEN A TOUGH DAY
AND A HALF FOR ME.
I BURNT MY FOOT
AND COOKED MY SNEAKERS.
>> COOKED YOUR SHOE!
TOO BAD WE CAN'T EAT YOUR SHOE.
FILLET OF SOLE.
(\LAUGHS\).
>> THAT'S PRETTY FUNNY.
WE DON'T GET FOOD SOON WE'RE
GOING TO BE EATING MY FOOT.
THIS PLACE IS GOD FORSAKEN.
>> IT IS. IT'S JINXED.
>> FOOD IS A HUGE ISSUE.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
OUR BAY THAT WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO DO THE FISHING IN
IS COMPLETELY WASHED OUT
SO WE HAVE...
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE LAZING
AROUND WAITING FOR FOOD TO COME.
WE HAVE NO FOOD
AND NO MEANS OF GETTING IT.
SO WE'RE DOWN TO TWO CUPS
OF RICE A DAY
AND OUR RATIONS IS
PROBABLY GOING TO PUT US DOWN
MORE THAN THAT.
SO, YEAH, WE'RE STARVING
AND WE'RE PRETTY SICK ABOUT IT.
>> HE'S JUST DOING...
THAT'S WHAT WE SHOULD BE DOING.
HE WAITS UNTIL THE FISH
COMES DOWN, WAITS FOR THEM,
SNAGS 'EM WHEN HE SEES HIM
AND THAT'S HOW WE SHOULD BE
FISHING RIGHT NOW.
>> WE REALLY NEED
TO CATCH SOME FISH TODAY.
>> YEAH, HE'S DOING IT.
LOOK, THAT WASN'T HARD.
AND THAT'S ALL WE NEED TO DO
IS SET OUT A NET THERE.
OKAY, JANE, I HAVEN'T TRIED
THROWING THIS YET.
I'M GOING TO SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
>> WE CAN TRY TO THROW IT
WITH THE TWO OF US.
>> WELL, THERE'S GUYS
THAT DO IT IN THE REAL WORLD,
THROW IT WITH ONE GUY.
>> I KNOW, BUT I'M NOT ONE
OF THOSE GUYS, MAYBE YOU ARE.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH...
THAT WAS GOING TO WORK
IF IT DIDN'T HIT MY FOOT.
I'LL TRY A COUPLE TIMES,
SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NOTHING.
>> I DO BELIEVE EVERY ONE OF US
IS GOING TO MISS JIMMY JOHNSON.
I MEAN, I'M GOING TO MISS HIM
BECAUSE HE WAS AS GOOD
A FISHERMAN AS ANYBODY.
BUT EVERY TEAM I'VE EVER BEEN ON
HAD A CAPTAIN AND A CO-CAPTAIN
AND THEY MADE DECISIONS BASED
UPON THE ABILITY OF THE TRIBE.
AND I'M HOPING
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO STEP UP
AND SAY "I WANT THAT ROLE."
>> I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THAT IT RAINED LAST NIGHT
UNTIL I WOKE UP THIS MORNING
AND I TRIED TO CLIMB OUT
OF THE SHELTER
AND IT WAS A LITTLE WET.
I SLEPT THAT WELL.
>> IS THAT THING OUT?
>> PRETTY MUCH.
>> BRENDA HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE RIGHT NOW
AND SHE'S BEEN TRYING
TO DECIPHER IT.
>> DIG EIGHT YARDS WEST.
TREE-MAIL?
>> WE'RE GOING TO TRY TO LOOK
FOR IT TODAY
BUT THESE CLUES ARE REALLY,
REALLY HARD TO FIGURE OUT.
>> MAYBE IT'S TREE-MAIL.
SO, UM, REMEMBER
HOW THE CLUE SHOWS THE TREE
AND THE GUY NEXT TO THE TREE?
AND IT HAS THE SUN, RIGHT?
SO IT'S WEST.
>> YOU ARE GOOD!
>> SO MAYBE LIKE ALIGN YOURSELF
WITH THE TREE AND THE SUN
SO THAT YOU'RE RIGHT IN FRONT
OF IT AND THAT'S WHERE YOU DIG.
DIG EIGHT YARDS WEST
OF TREE-MAIL.
>> WEST IS THAT WAY
SO IT'S LIKE IN THE BUSHES.
>> LOOK, WEST...
>> LOOK AROUND, LOOK AROUND.
>> IT'S RIGHT THERE?
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE!
>> GET IT! GET IT!
OH, MY GOD!
>> WHERE ARE WE GOING TO PUT IT?
>> OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
IT'S THE KEY TO OUR LIFE
IN THE GAME.
THE IMMUNITY IDOL IS MINE, MINE,
IT DOESN'T BELONG
TO ANYONE ELSE.
BRENDA HELPED ME FIND IT
BUT ULTIMATELY I FIGURED IT OUT
AND IT'S MINE.
>> THAT WAS CRAZY.
>> THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
IS IN MY SOCK.
IT'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
I CAME ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
FROM SOUTH CENTRAL L.A.
AND I THINK IT'S STARTING TO
FINALLY HIT ME THAT, YOU KNOW,
IT'S A MILLION DOLLARS
ON THE LINE,
ON THE LINE.
>> WHEN YOU FIND
THE IMMUNITY IDOL
YOU JUST DON'T TELL ANYBODY.
>> AND THAT WOULD NOT LET ANYONE
STAND IN MY WAY.
NOT EVEN A ONE-LEGGED PERSON CAN
STAND IN MY WAY AS YOU CAN SEE.
ONE SHOVE SHE'S OUT OF HERE.
>> IT'S LONELY OUT HERE.
>> THE HARDEST THING
FOR ME RIGHT NOW
IS TO PRETEND THAT I LIKE NAY.
UGH.
YOU KNOW?
>> I KNOW.
>> KELLY B. AND I HAVE REALLY
BUILT A GOOD RELATIONSHIP.
I REALLY LIKE HER.
SHE'S SUCH A NICE PERSON AND
SEEING THE WAY NAY TREATS HER,
IT MAKES ME SO FURIOUS.
SHE TACKLED A GIRL WITH ONE LEG.
LIKE HOW SICK IS THAT?
HOW CAN IT BE REALLY
THAT HARD TO FIND?
>> THE CLUES DON'T HELP.
NOR DOES LIKE SEARCHING
EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW?
>> WE HAVE TO FIND IT.
>> I KNOW WHERE THEY WENT.
I SAW THEIR FOOTSTEPS.
THEY WERE OVER IN THIS AREA.
AND THEY WERE, LIKE, THAT'S
THE ONLY PLACE THEY WERE AT.
SOMETHING'S OVER HERE.
>> I'VE BEEN WATCHING
ALINA AND KELLY B.
RUNNING LIKE A WILD BANSHEE
LOOKING
FOR THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO FIND IT.
THE IDOL'S ALREADY FOUND
AND IT'S HIDDEN.
SO WHAT DO I HAVE
TO LOSE RIGHT NOW? NOTHING.
SO I'M GOING TO TRY TO SCARE
THEM BECAUSE THEY'RE WEAK.
IF YOU GET IN THEIR HEAD
AND THEY'RE SCARED,
THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO KNOW WHAT TO DO.
YOU GUYS LOOKING FOR SOMETHING?
>> NO SECRET, LOOKING FOR THE
SAME THING YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
>> SO IF YOU SEE ME
WATCHING YOU GUYS...
>> FOLLOW US.
>> WHAT?
YOU KNOW I DON'T LIKE YOU.
NEVER HAVE LIKED YOU.
DON'T TRUST YOU.
>> NAONKA IS PSYCHO.
KELLY B. NEVER DID ANYTHING
TO NAY.
NEVER.
EXCEPT FOR GO FOR THE SAME CLUE.
>> I KNOW THAT LITTLE
PERFORMANCE YOU PUT ON
AFTER THAT [NO AUDIO] WENT DOWN.
I KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I JUST PUSHED YOU.
>> YOU KNOCKED ME OVER?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH!
>> BUT YOU SAID
I DON'T KNOW WHY SHE DID IT.
I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
NAY'S A BULLY.
I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE
TO CALL SOMEONE
WHO KNOCKS YOU OVER.
I DON'T KNOW
IF SHE'S WORRIED ABOUT ME
FINDING SOMETHING OUT THERE,
BUT SHE WANTED
A REACTION OUT OF ME,
I WASN'T GOING TO GIVE IT TO HER
BUT AT THE SAME TIME IT'S REALLY
HARD TO, LIKE, CONTAIN YOURSELF.
>> YOU'RE IN THE OUTS.
I'M NOT WITH YOU, SO...
>> WHY AM I ON THE OUTS?
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO EXPLAIN ANYTHING.
>> I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO EXPLAIN ANYTHING TO YOU.
I REALLY DON'T NEED
NO CHARITY CASE ON THE JURY,
BECAUSE FOR SURE, FOR SURE,
SHE WILL NOT VOTE FOR ME
TO GET THE MILLION DOLLARS.
CONTINUE LOOKING.
>> WHY DO YOU FEEL THAT WAY?
>> GOOD LUCK LOOKING FOR IT.
TORTURING KELLY B.
MENTALLY MIGHT EVEN FORCE HER
TO JUST QUIT THE GAME.
AND SCREW YOUR LEG.
SCREW YOUR LEG.
KEEP IT AWAY FROM THE FIRE.
>> YOU KNOW, WE'RE GETTING
THROUGH IT, AND, QUITE FRANKLY,
I COULDN'T SPEND TEN DAYS WITH
NO FOOD WITH MY FAMILY OUT HERE
WITHOUT KILLING ONE OF THEM, SO
I THINK WE'RE DOING REALLY GOOD.
>> I THINK WE ARE,
'CAUSE IT'S BEEN...
IT DOESN'T GET MUCH TOUGHER
THAN THIS, GUYS.
>> YEAH, IT'S HUGE.
WE'RE DOING GOOD, AND WE'RE ONLY
GOING TO GET BETTER
AS TIME MOVES FORWARD, I THINK.
WHAT...? ANY OTHER
OBSERVATIONS OTHER THAN...?
>> NO, I JUST THINK,
FOR THE CHALLENGE,
I THINK
IT'S IMPORTANT TO HAVE...
EITHER, FOR THE MOST PART,
ONE VOICE
THAT'S GOING TO DELEGATE
WHO'S GOING TO DO WHICH PARTS
OF THE CHALLENGE,
AND I THINK, YOU KNOW,
THE PERSON
THAT'S STUCK OUT THE MOST,
I THINK, IN TERMS
OF CONTRIBUTION OR WHATEVER,
HAS BEEN TYRONE.
SO, IF YOU WANT TO DO IT,
I WOULD NOMINATE YOU TO DO IT,
AND WE'VE GOT TO FALL IN LINE
AND JUST MAKE SURE
THAT EVERYONE LISTENS
AND IS OKAY WITH THAT, UM...
>> YOU KNOW, I'M JUST LISTENING
IN, AND IT'S TOUGH FOR ME.
AS YOU GUYS KNOW, I'VE SNAPPED
ON SEVERAL OTHER OCCASIONS.
I BARK ONCE IN A WHILE.
I'M A LEADER WHERE I COME FROM,
I LIKE TO BE A LEADER,
BUT IN THIS SITUATION, I REALLY
DON'T WANT TO BE THE LEADER,
AND I'M WILLING TO ACCEPT THAT.
I'M GOING TO SNAP ONCE
IN A WHILE,
AND SAY, "PLAY ME! PLAY ME!"
BUT IF YOU DON'T, THAT'S FINE,
I CAN ACCEPT THAT.
AND I'M WILLING
TO JUST PLAY MY ROLE.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE...
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, WE GO IN THE THING
AND NOBODY SAYS ANYTHING...
>> I'M ALWAYS GIVING
MY OPINION.
>> IF YOU THINK YOU'RE REALLY
GOOD AT ONE PART OF IT,
SAY, "OKAY, I'M READY,
I'LL BE THE GUY TO TAKE
A PUZZLE ON." OR WHATEVER.
>> MARTY'S DEFINITELY NOT
A BIG JIMMY T. FAN.
IT HAS TO STEM
FROM INSECURITIES,
'CAUSE I'M AN EASYGOING GUY.
YOU KNOW,
HE WANTS ULTIMATE CONTROL,
AND NOBODY SAY ANYTHING,
AND ANY TIME I TRY
TO GIVE SOME INPUT,
HE TRIES TO MILDLY,
HUMBLY SHOOT IT DOWN.
>> SO I DON'T KNOW ABOUT DOING
DEEP, DEEP ASSESSMENTS ABOUT,
YOU KNOW, HEY,
"WHAT DO YOU DO THE 40 IN?
AND WHO DOES, YOU KNOW,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
>> A COUPLE TIMES,
I'D LIKE TO TELL MARTY,
"WILL YOU SHUT UP,
YOU PREPPY LITTLE BITCH?
YOU WOULDN'T LAST A MINUTE
IN MY WORLD."
>> BUT PEOPLE SHOULD SAY
WHAT THEY FEEL
THEY'RE GOOD AT OR WHATEVER,
AND THEN, YOU GOT
TO BE THE TIE-BREAKER.
>> I'VE GOT TO GIVE HIM
A LITTLE SHAKE.
"MARTY! GET A CLUE!"
HEY, BUT MAYBE ONCE I LOSE IT,
THAT'S THE NEXT THING I'LL DO.
(\MONKEY HOWLING\)
>> TREE MAIL.
"LIFE, HOME AND FAMILY,
TRIBAL TOGETHERNESS AND TRUST.
"ONLY TEAM WORK CAN WIN WARMTH
AND COMFORT
OR YOUR EFFORTS WILL BE A BUST."
>> OH, YEAH.
>> BLINDFOLD. UH-OH.
>> BLINDFOLD.
SOMEBODY'S GOING
TO HAVE TO GUIDE.
>> OH.
>> WE SHOULD PRACTICE.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> JUST TO GET USED
TO BEING BLINDFOLD...
>> BEING BLINDFOLDED.
>> ...AND TAKING DIRECTION
AND WALKING BLIND OUT THERE.
>> YOU KNOW, IF WE GET ALL USED
TO THOSE DIRECTIONS,
WHEN YOU GIVE THE DIRECTIONS,
WE'LL KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU MEAN.
>> UH, JILL,
TEN STEPS STRAIGHT AHEAD.
DAN, 15 STEPS STRAIGHT AHEAD.
YEAH, WE'VE GOT TO GET THE "W,"
AND THE OTHER TRIBE
IS NOT A FACTOR TO ME.
JILL, STOP.
JILL, RIGHT TWO.
DAN, STOP. DAN, RIGHT THREE.
AND I'M CONFIDENT THAT IF
WE GIVE 110% OF OUR BEST EFFORT,
WHICH IS DISCIPLINE
AND LISTENING, I THINK
WE'LL DO BETTER, BECAUSE WE'RE
TYPICALLY MORE DISCIPLINED.
WE'RE OLDER.
>> EVERYBODY, WHEN HE GIVES
THE INSTRUCTION, RIGHT,
HE'S GOING TO GIVE 15 STEPS
IN WHATEVER DIRECTION,
YOU GOT TO DO THAT AND YOU GOT
TO STOP WITHOUT HIM SAYING STOP.
>> YES.
>> BECAUSE THEN HE'S GOING
TO GO TO THE NEXT PERSON,
AND YOU'RE GONNA BE...
'CAUSE YOU CAN'T JUST WAIT
AND WORK ON ONE PERSON.
YOU GOT TO BE MULTITASKING.
>> I NOMINATED TYRONE LAST NIGHT
AS THE LEADER FOR THE CHALLENGE,
AND, BY THE WAY,
I KNEW IT WOULD RILE JIMMY T.
YOU KNOW, HE'S LIKE
A THREE-YEAR-OLD.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> J.T. IS DELUSIONAL.
HE HAS NO IDEA.
HE SUFFERS FROM BOTH PARANOIA
AND FROM DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR.
>> HE DOESN'T NEED
TO TELL YOU...
>> DON'T TURN
IN THAT DIRECTION...
>> JANE, WELL, DO WHATEVER
INSTRUCTION HE DOES,
AND THEN,
WE AUTOMATICALLY STOP AND WAIT
FOR THE NEXT INSTRUCTION.
>> ANYBODY THAT CALLS OUT
JIMMY JOHNSON,
AND SAYS THAT JIMMY JOHNSON
MIGHT BE INSECURE
BECAUSE OF JIMMY T.'S LEADERSHIP
CAPABILITIES
HAS GOT SOME ISSUES GOING ON.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOUNGER TRIBE GETTING YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW OLDER TRIBE.
JIMMY JOHNSON VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
(gasping)
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY
TO GET TO TODAY'S CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
I WILL TAKE BACK IMMUNITY.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
ONE PERSON FROM EACH TRIBE
WILL BE YOUR CALLER.
THE REST OF THE TRIBE WILL BE
BLINDFOLDED AND PAIRED UP.
USING ONLY VERBAL COMMANDS,
THE CALLER WILL DIRECT
THEIR TRIBE MATES
TO COLLECT TEN ITEMS
SCATTERED IN THE FIELD.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL
TEN ITEMS BACK,
THE CALLER WILL THEN DIRECT ONE
PAIR OUT TO FIND A SET OF KEYS.
THOSE KEYS WILL UNLOCK A CHEST.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET THEIR CHEST
AND ALL TEN ITEMS BACK
TO THE START WINS IMMUNITY,
IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
IN ADDITION,
YOU ARE PLAYING FOR REWARD.
THE WINNING TRIBE WILL CHOOSE
THREE GROUPS OF ITEMS
FROM SEARS.
YOU HAVE A MASSIVE TOOL KIT,
TARP, ROPE, KNIFE,
A COMPLETE FISHING KIT.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NOW LET'S
GET TO THE MEDALLION OF POWER.
YOUNGER TRIBE,
YOU STILL HAVE IT.
IF YOU USE IT
IN TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOUR ADVANTAGE WILL BE TO BEGIN
WITH TWO ITEMS
ALREADY BACK
AT YOUR STARTING MAT.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO FIGURE OUT
IF YOU WANT TO USE IT.
>> I THINK THAT
WE SHOULD USE IT. >> USE IT.
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE,
WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> I THINK WE'RE GOING
TO USE IT.
>> GONNA USE IT.
BENRY, GIVE IT
TO SOMEBODY
FROM THE OLDER TRIBE.
OLDER TRIBE NOW HAS
THE MEDALLION OF POWER
AND WILL GET A CHANCE TO USE IT
AT A FUTURE CHALLENGE.
THIS CHALLENGE RUNS
WITH ONLY SEVEN TRIBE MEMBERS.
OLDER TRIBE,
YOU'RE SITTING ONE PERSON OUT.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> DANIEL.
>> Jeff: DANIEL'S GONNA
SIT OUT FOR THE OLDER TRIBE?
YOUNGER TRIBE,
YOU'RE SITTING OUT TWO PEOPLE.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> THE TWO KELLYS.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SIT-OUTS,
TAKE A SEAT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL GIVE YOU
A MINUTE TO STRATEGIES.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, FOR THE YOUNGER
TRIBE, BRENDA IS THE CALLER.
FOR THE OLDER TRIBE,
TYRONE IS THE CALLER.
YOUNGER TRIBE STARTING WITH
TWO ITEMS ALREADY ON THEIR MAT.
MEANS THEY ONLY HAVE
TO COLLECT EIGHT ITEMS.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY? GO!
>> GROUP ONE, TWO,
THREE, GET GOING!
>> JILL, 20 STRAIGHT.
>> YOU'RE GOING
ALL THE WAY DOWN.
>> J.T., 20 STRAIGHT.
>> GROUP TWO TO FOUR,
GROUP THREE TO YOUR RIGHT.
GROUP THREE TO YOU RIGHT.
>> AAH! >> GROUP THREE, RIGHT.
>> KEEP GOING STRAIGHT
ALL OF YOU. KEEP GOING STRAIGHT.
>> JILL, STOP!
LEFT THREE.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY BLINDFOLDED.
>> GROUP TWO,
STOP WHERE YOU ARE, GROUP ONE...
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY TRYING
TO GET THEIR BEARINGS.
>> HEY, STOP! TEAM, STOP!
TURN AROUND! REVERSE.
FORWARD. THREE.
>> GROUP THREE, FORWARD.
FEEL THAT, FEEL THAT
ON YOUR LEFT. >> REVERSE!
>> GET THE TARP! IT'S ON
YOUR LEFT! EVERYONE, STOP!
>> JILL, FORWARD. THREE.
>> GROUP THREE, GET... YES, YES!
COME BACK...
>> JIMMY T., LEFT, FIVE!
>> GROUP TWO TO YOUR LEFT...
>> Jeff: BRENDA VERY CALM AS SHE
DIRECTS THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
>> STOP! STOP, JILL!
PUT YOUR HANDS DOWN.
>> GO THREE, YES, TWO, YES.
ALL THREE, COME BACK.
>> OBJECTIVE TO THE RIGHT.
OBJECTIVE RIGHT!
COME BACK, YVE, REVERSE.
REVERSE.
>> ALL THREE COME BACK...
>> Jeff: THE YOUNGER TRIBE OFF
TO A QUICK START.
THREE ITEMS, RACING BACK.
>> COME ON.
>> GO BACK.
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE STARTED
WITH AN ADVANTAGE OF TWO ITEMS.
NAONKA AND ALINA WITH THE FIFTH
ITEM FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
OLDER TRIBE COMING BACK
WITH THEIR FIRST ITEM.
MARTY TAKES A FALL.
>> YVE, STOP! GRAB IT.
TURN AROUND!
COME BACK, YVE!
>> ALL THREE KEEP GOING!
>> COME STRAIGHT BACK, BLUE!
>> CHASE,
ON YOUR LEFT-HAND SIDE.
>> AAH!
>> CHASE, ON YOUR LEFT.
CHASE, GRAB THE TOP!
>> I GOT IT. BRENDA?!
>> YES! BRING IT BACK, YES!
YES!
>> STOP IT...
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE
WITH THEIR FIRST ITEM.
YOUNGER TRIBE COMING BACK
WITH THEIR SIXTH ITEM.
>> STOP!
>> DROP IT! GO TO YOUR LEFT.
>> JIMMY T., BACK UP.
BACK UP, JIMMY T., THREE.
>> MAKE SURE...
>> JIMMY, THAT'S IT.
GRAB IT! GRAB IT! TURN AROUND!
>> IS THIS ONE?
>> STOP, DROP IT, JILL.
>> Jeff: MARTY AND JILL DROP THE
SECOND ITEM FOR THE OLDER TRIBE.
>> ALINA, YOU GOT IT.
BRING THAT BACK.
>> YVE, STAND UP,
TURN RIGHT THREE...
>> Jeff: SEVEN ITEMS
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
>> 20'S GREAT, JIMMY T.
>> GO BACK ON YOUR LEFT.
>> HEY, I GOT A TARP!
>> YES, BEN, YES!
BRING IT BACK! BRING IT BACK!
>> FABIO, SHE SAID YES!
>> OH!
>> JILL, JILL, FIVE FORWARD.
GO JILL!
>> Jeff:
YVE AND JANE COMING BACK
WITH ANOTHER ITEM
FOR THE OLDER TRIBE.
THAT'S THREE ITEMS
THAT'S THE EIGHTH ITEM
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
TWO ITEMS LEFT.
YOUNGER TRIBE WITH A HUGE LEAD.
>> JIMMY T., RIGHT!
JIMMY T., RIGHT!
>> I GOT TO GO THIS WAY.
COME THIS WAY.
>> Jeff: NINE ITEMS
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
>> DROP IT THERE.
SASH, BRING THAT BACK!
>> OVER HERE.
>> BRING THAT BACK DOWN!
>> IS IT THIS HERE?
>> BRING IT BACK. YES!
>> GO.
>> SASH, BRING IT BACK!
>> Jeff: SASH AND CHASE HAVE
THE TENTH AND FINAL ITEM
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE!
>> DROP IT. DROP IT.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T. AND HOLLY DROP
THE FOURTH ITEM
FOR THE OLDER TRIBE.
>> GO STRAIGHT.
STOP, JILL!
TURN LEFT THREE.
STRAIGHT! NO, LEFT, JILL. STOP.
>> Jeff: YVE AND JANE WITH FIVE
FOR THE OLDER TRIBE.
>> GO BACK OUT, STOP.
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE
HAS ALL TEN ITEMS.
NOW THEY'VE GOT
TO FIND THE SET OF KEYS...
>> GO TO THE KEYS.
>> Jeff: ...TO UNLOCK THE CHEST.
>> GO TO YOUR LEFT, CHASE!
TO YOUR LEFT!
>> YVE, STOP!
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE
IN HUGE TROUBLE RIGHT NOW.
>> YVE, GO RIGHT!
>> IS HE TALKING TO US?
>> JIMMY T., GO RIGHT!
>> MOVE TO YOUR LEFT!
TO YOUR LEFT!
TO YOUR LEFT! GET THE TREE!
YES, YES, YES, YES!
>> JIMMY T., GO RIGHT 20!
>> Jeff: SASH AND CHASE HAVE
THE KEYS TO THE CHEST NOW.
>> KEEP GOING FORWARD!
THE CHEST IS IN FRONT OF YOU.
>> YVE! YVE, TURN AROUND, STOP.
>> THERE YOU GO, UNLOCK IT.
>> Jeff: HOLLY, JIMMY T.
HAVE BEEN WANDERING...
>> STOP, JIMMY T.!
STOP, JIMMY!
>> Jeff: ...FOR A LONG TIME
WITH NO IDEA...
>> JIMMY, STOP!
DAMN, THAT BOY DON'T LISTEN!
JIMMY T.!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE
HAS THEIR BLOCK UNDONE.
>> BRING IT BACK TO ME.
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE
HAS THE CHEST.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK
FOR THE WIN!
>> YVE, STOP MOVING! YVE!
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE
IN COMPLETE DISARRAY.
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> GO RIGHT! TURN RIGHT!
>> KEEP GOING STRAIGHT.
>> JIMMY T...
>> HERE! UP HERE! ON THE
PLATFORM! ON THE PLATFORM!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE WINS
IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
>> WHEN I WAS OVER THERE,
I COULDN'T HEAR YOU
OVER EVERYBODY ELSE
SCREAMING AND YELLING, SO...
(cheering)
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY ONCE AGAIN.
(\APPLAUSE\)
IN ADDITION, YOU NOW GET
TO SELECT THREE GROUPS OF ITEMS
FROM SEARS TO TAKE WITH YOU
BACK TO CAMP.
WHAT ARE THE THREE GROUPS?
>> FISHING, THE TARP
AND THE COOKING SUPPLIES.
>> ALL RIGHT,
COME GET YOUR ITEMS.
PUT THEM IN YOUR CRATE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, OLDER TRIBE,
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FOURTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> IT WAS REALLY TOUGH.
I MEAN, IT WASN'T EASY,
YOU KNOW?
AND I DON'T KNOW IF I WAS IN IT
I DON'T THINK
IT WOULD HAVE MATTERED.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS JUST TOUGH.
IT WAS JUST TOUGH.
I KNOW I'M NOT GOOD ON MUD
SO I'M NOT A MUDDER,
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE POWER
OF THE MEDALLION REALLY DID IT.
>> YEAH, AND THAT ALONE SAYS
SOMETHING ABOUT US, YOU KNOW?
THEY NEEDED AN ADVANTAGE
TO BEAT US.
>> UM, IT'S GOOD TO SIT HERE
AND SAY WELL, WE DID GOOD,
WE DID GOOD.
BUT, LOOK, I'M GOING TO CONTINUE
TO ASK TO GET A LITTLE ACTION.
I THINK I CAN CONTRIBUTE.
I'M...
I'VE COACHED BASKETBALL TEAMS
AND I'VE COACHED CREWS,
I CONTINUE TO COACH CHILDREN
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
I THINK I CAN BE A LEADER
IN IMMUNITY CHALLENGES
AND I'D LIKE THAT OPPORTUNITY.
>> SO TODAY DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
MORE VALUABLE SOMEWHERE ELSE?
>> UM, PROBABLY NOT.
I'M JUST LOOKING
FOR AN OPPORTUNITY
TO HELP THIS TEAM WIN.
I'VE BEEN SUCCESSFUL IN THE PAST
AND I CAN BE SUCCESSFUL
IN THE FUTURE.
I JUST WANT A FAIR OPPORTUNITY.
DOESN'T EVEN GET
AN EQUAL OPPORTUNITY?
>> JIMMY T.,
HE'S DIGGING HIS OWN HOLE.
EVERY TIME WE HAVE A CHALLENGE
HE'S VERY NEGATIVE AFTERWARDS.
VERY NEGATIVE HE SAYS
"ALL I WANT IS A SHOT.
"I CAN GET IN THERE,
I CAN MAKE SOME THINGS,
I'VE COACHED."
YOU KNOW, START GIVING ME
HIS RESUME.
BOTTOM LINE IS
HE'S VERY MUCH ABOUT HIM
AND IT'S BECOMING MORE
AND MORE CLEAR
AND THE COMMENTS TODAY
I DIDN'T DIG AT ALL.
>> WHAT!
>> A LOT OF GEAR IN THERE.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> GOOD JOB, EVERYBODY.
GOOD JOB.
>> GOD BLESS SEARS.
>> WHAT A WIN.
>> NEW KNIVES.
>> YEAH WE HAVE
A WHOLE KNIFE SET.
>> A WHOLE KNIFE SET.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WHAT WE WANTED MOST!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
A TARP, BABY!
WHOO!
>> WE CAN SLEEP NOW.
>> AS SOON AS I OPENED
THE TACKLE BOX
I SAW A ROLLED UP PIECE
OF PAPER.
I KNEW IT WAS A CLUE AND AS SOON
AS I SAW THAT I SHUT IT.
>> LET'S HAVE A LITTLE
WATERMELON CELEBRATION.
EVERYONE ELSE WENT OVER
AND LOOKED AT THE TARP
OR WHATEVER THEY WERE
LOOKING AT, I DIDN'T CARE.
I GRABBED THE NOTE,
FOLDED IT UP,
PUT IT IN MY POCKET AND...
BRENDA IS A VERY CLOSE ALLY
OF MINE.
I'D PROBABLY TRUST HER
MORE THAN ANYONE OUT HERE.
I HAVE A CLUE IN MY POCKET.
>> WHAT?
>> YEP.
I'M TELLING YOU THAT BECAUSE
I TRUST YOU, YOU KNOW?
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
SO NOW WHAT?
>> NOW WE LOOK FOR IT.
DIG EIGHT YARDS LEFT
OF TREE-MAIL.
>> LET'S GO.
>> IF WE CAN GET THIS IDOL,
WE'RE GOLD.
>> CHASE FOUND THE THIRD CLUE.
HE FIGURED OUT WHERE
IT SHOULD BE IF IT WAS THERE
AND I JUST FELT SO BAD
BECAUSE HE IS MY BUDDY.
DO YOU TRUST NAY?
>> DO YOU TRUST HER?
>> I TRUST HER.
>> YOU DO?
>> DO YOU TRUST ME?
>> I TRUST YOU.
>> WHO DO YOU TRUST MORE?
>> YOU.
>> LIKE HOW MUCH MORE?
>> I TRUST YOU MORE
THAN ANYONE HERE.
>> GOOD.
WELL, THEN I'VE GOT
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
>> WHAT?
IT'S EITHER EIGHT YARDS THAT WAY
OR EIGHT YARDS WEST.
DO YOU WANT TO LOOK AT THE CLUE?
>> OKAY, THIS IS THE THING.
YOU'RE NOT LISTENING TO ME.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> OKAY. UM...
SO IF NAY FOR WHATEVER REASON
CONFIDED IN ME
BECAUSE SHE REALLY DOES TRUST ME
AND I TRUST HER.
>> WHY ARE YOU WORRIED?
>> BECAUSE I AM TRYING TO KEEP
MY TRUST
WITH THE PERSON WHO HAS
THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> SOMEONE HAS
THE IMMUNITY IDOL?
WHO? NAY?
>> YEAH.
BUT I FOUND IT FOR HER.
>> YOU SWEAR TO ME?
>> I SWEAR TO YOU.
>> YOU GUYS FOUND IT?
>> I SWEAR TO YOU WE FOUND IT.
>> YOU CAN NOT TRUST ANYONE IN
THIS GAME
BUT SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO.
NAONKA AND I DON'T HAVE
A GREAT TRUST
BUT WE DO HAVE BRENDA
BETWEEN US, YOU KNOW?
SO AS LONG AS NAY'S
NOT COMING AFTER ME,
THEN THAT'S FINE.
CAN I DO THIS?
>> WHAT?
>> CAN I GO UP TO NAY
AND BE LIKE...
>> YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SAY ANYTHING.
SERIOUSLY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY ANYTHING.
IF WORD GETS OUT
THAT I TOLD CHASE,
NAY WON'T TRUST ME ANYMORE
BECAUSE I...
I BETRAYED HER TRUST.
WHICH IS BIG BECAUSE
SHE'S THE ONE WITH THE IDOL.
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
MY POSITION.
SHE HAS IT.
SO IF I BETRAY HER, WE'RE ALL--
ME, YOU-- ARE ALL SCREWED UP.
>> NOT A LOT
OF SEA URCHINS HERE.
>> THAT'S A BIG ONE, ISN'T IT?
>> YEAH GOOD ENOUGH.
YOU CAN GET SOMETHING
OUT OF THAT.
>> OH, WE'RE DIGGING AROUND
FOR SEA URCHINS.
WE'RE REALLY HURTING FOR FOOD
AND THIS IS ABOUT IT.
YOU GET TINY LITTLE GLOP
OF SALTY PROTEIN.
BUT IT'S REALLY GOOD.
THEY ACTUALLY ARE
JUST A BIT OF FLAVOR
AND YEAH,
WE'RE DOWN TO SEA URCHINS NOW.
>> MARTY, YOU'RE NOT
CONTRIBUTING TO THE COMPANY POT?
>> I JUST GRABBED TWO OR THREE
OF THE LITTLE TINY ONES.
>> TWO OR THREE OVER HERE,
TWO OR THREE OVER THERE
THEN TWO OR THREE OVER THERE.
WHAT ABOUT THE REST OF THE TEAM?
COME ON, MAN, BE A TRIBE PLAYER.
>> NOT GONNA GO THERE WITH YOU,
BUDDY.
YOU GUYS CAN EAT
ALL THE ONES YOU CAUGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE
DOING THE RIGHT THING.
>> APPRECIATE THAT.
TRYING TO CALL ME OUT
AS A NON-TEAM PLAYER
BECAUSE I ATE
A COUPLE SEA URCHINS
AND I DIDN'T CONTRIBUTE
SEA URCHINS TO HIS NET,
HE JUST DOESN'T GET THIS GAME.
YOU DO THAT,
THAT'S THE PERFECT WAY TO ENSURE
YOUR DESTINY IN THIS GAME.
>> OH, BACK THERE HE WAS LIKE...
>> OH, WITH THE...
>> YOU EATING THE URCHINS
ALL BY YOURSELF.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE A TEAM PLAYER.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
>> YOU ARE.
DON'T WORRY, YOU ARE.
>> OF COURSE I KNOW THAT.
SO JIMMY T. TRYING TO TELL ME
THAT I'M NOT A TEAM PLAYER
AND CALLING IT OUT
IN FRONT OF THE WHOLE TRIBE?
THAT'S THE EQUIVALENT OF PUTTING
A GUN TO YOUR MOUTH,
PULLING THE TRIGGER AND BLOWING
YOUR BRAINS OUT
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
>> I'M GOING TO WRITE
DANNY'S NAME DOWN.
I DON'T WANT
TO BUT I'M GOING TO.
I THINK HE'S BEEN
HITTING AROUND.
HE'S HAD ENOUGH.
DON'T YOU?
I'M GOING TO HATE LOSING DANNY
BECAUSE I LOVE
HIS LITTLE ONE-LINERS.
>> SO DO I.
>> I MEAN, I DO.
>> SO YOU THINK THAT'S
WHO YOU'LL VOTE FOR?
>> YEAH.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT COACH
PUT DOWN
AND I THINK COACH WAS SENDING
A MESSAGE TO US
TO VOTE
THE NEXT WEAKEST LINK OUT.
>> HONESTLY I THINK WE'LL KEEP
DAN AROUND AFTER TODAY.
HE ALWAYS SITS OUT.
>> WE HAVE TO.
WE HAVE TO.
IT'S CRITICAL.
HE'S OUR SWING VOTE.
>> I DON'T THINK I'VE GOT
28 MORE DAYS OF THIS IN ME.
>> JUST TAKE IT ONE DAY
AT A TIME.
TAKE IT ONE DAY AT A TIME.
BUT JIMMY T.
FOR SURE, RIGHT?
CORRECT?
>> WHATEVER YOU SAY.
>> WE'VE GOT TO WORK ON TYRONE,
OKAY?
THAT'S THE KEY, RIGHT?
>> I'LL TALK TO HIM.
>> THE MAIN THING IS THAT
DANNY DOES NOT GO HOME.
I TRIED TO DRILL THAT INTO JILL.
I THINK SHE GETS IT.
DO I WISH DANNY WAS STRONGER
AND BETTER?
IT WOULD BE GREAT
BUT AFTER TONIGHT
PEOPLE WILL UNDERSTAND IT
DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT THEY WANT TO SAY ABOUT
WHETHER DANNY'S WEAK
AND WHY AM I PROTECTING HIM.
>> STUFF'S TOO WET.
>> IT WILL BE NUMBERS.
NUMBERS SPEAK FOR THEMSELVES
AND THE NUMBERS WILL DICTATE
THE OUTCOME
OF THE NEXT THREE TRIBALS
AND I KNOW I CAN COUNT ON HIM.
I KNOW I CAN COUNT ON HIM.
>> HEY, LOOK AT THIS.
>> WOULD YOU STOP?
>> CAN YOU HELP ME UNTIE
THE SHOES?
>> JIMMY T.
DRIVES US ALL CRAZY.
HE DRIVES EVERYBODY CRAZY
IN CAMP.
IT'S JUST...
IT'S ANNOYING AS ALL HELL
AND IF I DON'T HAVE
TO LISTEN TO HIM
AT ANY MORE TRIBAL COUNCILS,
IT WILL BE A BLESSING.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S A TOSSUP BETWEEN DANNY
AND JIMMY T.
>> IF I'D GIVE YOU MY DRUTHERS
I'D PICK JIMMY T.
>> OKAY, GIVEN MY DRUTHERS
I'D PICK DAN
BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS...
EVERYTHING REQUIRES SOMETHING.
DAN'S HAVING A HARD TIME
WALKING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I HELP HIM THROUGH EVERYTHING.
YEAH, HE'S A GREAT GUY
AND HE'S STILL GOING TO BE
A GREAT GUY BUT YOU'RE NOT...
YOU KNOW,
HELPING OUR CAUSE RIGHT NOW.
>> RIGHT.
>> HONESTLY, I WANT DAN
TO GO BUT HE'S...
BECAUSE I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
FOR A STRONG TEAM
BUT HE'S INTRINSIC
TO MY ALLIANCE
SO I'M NOT SURE I CAN DO THAT.
I MEAN, I LOVE DAN BUT HE'S
DEFINITELY THE GUY
WHO SITS EVERY GAME
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
>> DID HE SAY ANYTHING?
>> HE WANTS DAN.
>> HE WANTS WHAT?
>> DAN. HE THINKS DAN'S WEAK.
HE'S ALL ABOUT A STRONG TEAM.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN
SWING HIM SO I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T WANT
TO VOTE DANNY OUT.
I'M TELLING YOU.
ARE YOU LEANING TOWARDS ONE
OR THE OTHER RIGHT NOW?
>> YEAH.
IT'S KIND OF CRAZY.
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS DANNY
WAS MY FIRST THOUGHT.
HIS KNEES,
HE CAN'T RUN IN THE MUD.
EVERYTHING WE'VE DONE HAS BEEN
IN THE MUD TO SOME DEGREE,
YOU KNOW?
>> A LITTLE BIT,
YEAH, I HEAR YOU.
I JUST THINK SOMETIMES
THERE'S THINGS
THAT ARE JUST WRONG,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S LIKE A CANCER.
TO BE HONEST, RIGHT NOW
I'D RATHER HAVE JIMMY T. GONE.
AND I FEEL PRETTY STRONGLY
ABOUT HAVING SOMEBODY
THAT'S THAT VOLATILE
AND THAT LOOSE.
AND IT'S PUSHING THE BOUNDARIES
OF MY PATIENCE
BUT, UM, YEAH, HIS PLEA,
HIS BIGGEST FEEDBACK
AFTER THE CHALLENGE TODAY
WAS THAT HE WANTS
TO BE THE LEADER,
BASICALLY, IS WHAT HE'S SAYING.
THE GUY'S A TRAIN WRECK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE COULD LEAD ANYTHING.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL I WANT IS A SHOT
AT ONE CHALLENGE.
ONE SHOT; ONE CHALLENGE.
THAT'S ALL.
I DON'T WANT TO BE LEADER.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE
DONE DIFFERENTLY?
>> I'M NOT SAYING I WOULD HAVE
DONE ANYTHING DIFFERENT
OR I COULD HAVE WON TODAY.
I JUST WOULD HAVE LIKED
THE OPPORTUNITY.
THE QUESTION IS
WHY AREN'T I GETTING THE CHANCE?
WHY IS EVERYBODY SAYING HEY,
LET ME GET A CHANCE.
NO, NO, NO.
WHY IS THAT?
>> YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES SILENCE
IS A LITTLE BIT MORE POWERFUL
THAN SPEAKING
AND IT'S A SOCIAL GAME, TOO,
AND I KNOW J.T. APPEARS VERBALLY
TO BE SECURE BUT HE'S INSECURE.
>> I'VE GOT TO BE ME.
I'M GOING TO CONTINUE TO SAY
"PLEASE CAN I HAVE MY CHANCE?"
>> AND WHEN SOMEONE
OF THAT STATURE
AND THAT ACCOMPLISHMENT
DOESN'T TRUST HE'S ENOUGH,
IS HE...
I CAN'T TRUST HE'S GOING
TO BE ENOUGH DOWN THE ROAD.
>> ANYWAY, THANKS FOR LISTENING.
I...
SEND ME YOUR THERAPY BILL
AND I APPRECIATE YOU HEARING ME.
>> I'M A MOTHER
AND I DON'T CODDLE MY KIDS
THAT MUCH.
>> YOU NEVER KNOW IN THIS GAME.
I'M SCARED IT MIGHT BE ME
BECAUSE I KEEP OPENING MY MOUTH.
I'M GETTING A LITTLE MESSY.
CAN YOU PASS ME THE NAPKINS,
PLEASE?
BUT OF COURSE EVERY TIME
I OPEN MY MOUTH
ABOUT "PUT ME IN, COACH"
IT FALLS ON DEAF EARS.
THEY DON'T TALK MUCH TO ME.
I GET VERY LITTLE OUT OF THEM.
THAT'S WHAT FEEDS MY FUEL
OF FEELING LIKE I'M ALL ALONE
ON A PLANET HERE.
IT'S A TOUGH GROUP OF PEOPLE
TO GET ALONG WITH.
AND I'M EASY TO GET ALONG WITH,
I THINK.
>> Jeff: TYRONE, LET'S TALK
ABOUT TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> TODAY WE WENT WITH OUR PLAN.
WORKED OUT WELL.
I THINK THE MEDALLION
OF POWER...
>> Jeff: WAIT.
YOUR PLAN FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
WORKED OUT WELL?
>> WELL, PROVIDED THE MEDALLION
OF POWER WASN'T IN THE PLAY
I THINK IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A
MUCH MORE COMPETITIVE CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: MARTY, IS THAT
YOUR TAKE AS WELL?
>> YEAH, WE HAD ONE MORE ITEM
TO GO,
THEY HAD TWO TO START OUT WITH
SO AT THE VERY LEAST
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A CLOSE MATCH
OR WE COULD HAVE HAD A LEG UP.
>> Jeff: TO BE CLEAR,
YOU HAD ONE MORE ITEM,
A SET OF KEYS, A CHEST,
THREE LOCKS AND GETTING IT BACK.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S BEHIND US;
WE'VE GOT TO MOVE FORWARD.
FIXING WHAT WE CAN AT CAMP,
THAT'S THE MENTAL ATTITUDE
YOU HAVE TO HAVE.
>> Jeff: DAN, YOU SAT
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE YET AGAIN.
>> I TOLD EVERYBODY ON THE TRIBE
THAT I DO NOT FEEL COMFORTABLE
BECAUSE OF MY KNEE SLOSHING
AROUND IN MUD.
IF YOU PUT ME ON LEVEL GROUND,
I'LL GO UP AGAINST ANYBODY.
BUT WHY WOULD I WANT
TO DO SOMETHING
THAT I KNOW I'M NOT GOOD AT
AND POSSIBLY HURT THE TRIBE?
>> Jeff: NO, I WOULDN'T EITHER.
BUT WHEN YOU COME
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL SAYING
"I CAN'T GO BECAUSE IT'S MUDDY"
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE RAIN FOREST,
YOU HAVE TO BE A LITTLE WORRIED
THAT MAYBE
I'M JUST TOO MUCH OF A BURDEN.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YEAH, MAYBE I AM.
>> Jeff: DO YOU BELIEVE YOU ARE?
>> NO.
IF I THINK I'M MAKING THE PROPER
CHOICE OF SITTING DOWN,
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
AND I'LL DO IT AGAIN.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT THE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: JILL, HOW MUCH
DOES THAT FACTOR IN FOR YOU
WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT WHO TO VOTE OUT TONIGHT?
>> IT'S...
IT FACTORS IN A LOT
IN MY THINKING.
I MEAN, I KNOW EVERYONE'S
KIND OF LIKE,
RAH, RAH, WE DID OUR BEST,
BUT I'M TIRED OF LOSING.
I'M NOT USED TO LOSING.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
WE'VE GONE
THROUGH AN N.F.L. COACH
AND ALL THIS STUFF
AND WE'RE STILL NOT
WINNING CHALLENGES
AND IT'S BUGGING ME.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T., JILL MENTIONS
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
AN N.F.L. COACH, GOT RID OF HIM.
HOW FRUSTRATING IS THAT
TO NOT HAVE LEADERSHIP?
>> RIGHT.
THE SHIP IS GOING DOWN.
WE KEEP COMING BACK HERE
VOTING GUYS OUT,
SO WHY DON'T WE TRY
MIXING IT UP?
>> Jeff: AND "MIXING IT UP"
WOULD MEAN WHAT?
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS
I'VE BEEN VOCAL
IN WANTING ONE OPPORTUNITY
TO LEAD THE TRIBE
IN AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
BUT I CONTINUE TO BE
THE SQUEAKY WHEEL
THAT DOESN'T GET THE OIL.
>> Jeff: MARTY,
WHY NOT GIVE JIMMY T. A SHOT?
ARE YOU OPEN TO IT?
>> NOT NECESSARILY, NO.
I MEAN, I THINK AS A TRIBE,
WE THOUGHT THAT TYRONE SHOULD BE
THE GUY CALLING THE SHOTS.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S ALWAYS NECESSARILY
SOME INCREDIBLE
LEADERSHIP QUALITY.
I MEAN, WE HAD JIMMY JOHNSON
FOR... SAKE.
IT DOESN'T GET
ANY BETTER THAN THAT
WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT LEADERSHIP.
YOU'VE GOT
A STRESSFUL SITUATION HERE.
THERE IS ZERO TOLERANCE
FOR PARANOIA,
DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR,
POPPING OFF.
EVERYONE RIGHT NOW IS TRYING
TO BE AS PATIENT AS POSSIBLE,
BUT IT'S BEEN STRETCHED
TO THE LIMIT.
>> JEFF, I'M OFFERING.
THEY DON'T WANT TO ACCEPT,
THAT'S FINE.
BUT WHAT KIND OF SUCCESS IS
ESPADA TRIBE HAVING RIGHT NOW?
>> Jeff: VERY LITTLE.
>> CASE CLOSED.
>> YOU KNOW,
CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
ALL HE'S ASKING FOR IS A CHANCE.
LET HIM TRY.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT
THE SIXTH PERSON ON THE BENCH
DOESN'T HAVE THE ABILITY
AS THE FIRST PERSON ON THE BENCH
IF YOU DON'T GIVE HIM A CHANCE?
THAT'S THE WAY I LOOK AT IT.
>> LISTEN, I'M A VALUABLE
CONTRIBUTOR TO THE TRIBE.
I PROVIDE FOOD.
I TRY TO PROVIDE COMFORT,
BUT EVIDENTLY THEY DON'T SEE ME
THE SAME LIGHT I SEE ME.
>> Jeff: TYRONE, IF YOU BELIEVED
JIMMY T. COULD CHANGE,
IF YOU BELIEVED IT WAS POSSIBLE,
WOULD HE HAVE VALUE
TO THE TRIBE?
>> YEAH. HE HAS VALUE NOW
AS IT IS EVEN THOUGH
HE'S NOT A FOLLOWER.
HE WOULD HAVE MORE VALUE
IF HE WAS,
YOU KNOW, ABLE TO BE A FOLLOWER.
>> Jeff: OKAY. SO JIMMY T.,
ARE YOU WILLING TO ACCEPT
THE ROLE
THAT THIS TRIBE CLEARLY
WANTS YOU TO HAVE,
WHICH IS AS A FOLLOWER,
NOT A LEADER?
>> I'M MAN ENOUGH.
I BELIEVE I'M MAN ENOUGH.
AND MAYBE...
MAYBE THEY DON'T BELIEVE SO,
BUT I'M MAN ENOUGH
TO TAKE MY ROLE
AND TAKE SOME GOOD ADVICE.
>> Jeff: IS THIS HARD?
>> VERY HARD FOR ME.
>> Jeff: WHY DOES IT HURT
SO MUCH?
I CAN SEE YOU'RE EMOTIONAL.
>> GIVE ME A MINUTE.
>> I SAY TAKE THIS
AS AN OPPORTUNITY
TO HAVE THE COURAGE
TO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT,
HEY, MAYBE THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT I CAN DO
TO BE A BETTER ME
AND MOVE FORWARD FROM THERE.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T.,
FROM ALL GUYS,
TYRONE EXTENDING
THE OLIVE BRANCH.
>> I THINK THEY KNOW
I'M A MAN OF HONOR.
I KNOW I'M A MAN OF HONOR
AND INTEGRITY.
IF I SAY I'M GOING SOMETHING,
I'M GONNA HONOR THAT.
SO I'LL STEP DOWN AND SAY
I'LL JUST BE A WORKER BEE
FOR THIS TRIBE
AND A GOOD WORKER BEE
AND NOBODY CAN DENY THAT.
>> Jeff: WELL,
A LOT HAS BEEN SAID
AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE QUESTION IS,
HOW WILL IT IMPACT THE VOTE?
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
HOLLY, YOU'RE UP.
>> SORRY ABOUT YOUR SHOES,
BUT YOU SAT OUT TWO CHALLENGES.
YOU'RE THE WEAK ONE ON THE TEAM.
YOU NEED TO GO.
>> SEE YA, PAL.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
>> Jeff: ONCE THE VOTES
ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, DAN.
DAN.
TWO VOTES DAN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES DAN.
JIMMY T.
THREE VOTES DAN,
ONE VOTE JIMMY T.
JIMMY T.
THAT'S THREE VOTES DAN,
TWO VOTES JIMMY T.
JIMMY T.
WE'RE TIED, THREE VOTES DAN,
THREE VOTES JIMMY T.
JIMMY T.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JIMMY T.,
THREE VOTES DAN, ONE VOTE LEFT.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT
OF SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA,
JIMMY T.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T.,
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
WELL, IT SEEMS PRETTY CLEAR
THAT TONIGHT'S VOTE
WAS AN ATTEMPT TO IMPROVE
THE CHEMISTRY OF THIS TRIBE.
LET'S HOPE IT WORKED,
BECAUSE SOMETHING
HAS GOT TO CHANGE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUT NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME
ON SURVIVOR...
NAONKA BECOMES
HER OWN WORST ENEMY.
>> STILL HURTING?
>> IT'S KILLING ME.
>> Jeff: AND MARTY'S
MILLION-DOLLAR DREAM RIDE...
>> IT WOULD TAKE
SOMETHING EXTRAORDINARY,
COMPLETELY WHACKED
OUT TO DISTURB MY PLAN.
>> Jeff: ...GRINDS TO A HALT.
DROP YOUR BUFFS.
IT IS A BRAND NEW GAME.
>> I WAS DEFINITELY
NOT COUNTING ON THIS.
>> YEAH, I TOTALLY BLEW MY GAME.
IT'S MY OWN FAULT.
I PLANNED ON KEEPING
MY MOUTH SHUT
AND THAT WENT RIGHT
OUT THE WINDOW.
I THINK MARTY'S
THE PUPPET MASTER
AND HE'S PULLING
ALL THE STRINGS RIGHT.
HE'S PLAYING WITH HIS HEAD.
I PLAYED WITH MY HEART.
DEFINITELY OUTWITTED ME.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'VE GOT TO DO
IN THIS GAME.
I JUST REALLY FEEL LIKE I BLEW
A TREMENDOUS OPPORTUNITY.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE
I LET PEOPLE DOWN.