>> Jeff:
PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR.
IN THE BATTLE
OF OLD VERSUS YOUNG,
THE YOUNGER TRIBE WAS THRIVING.
>> HANDS DOWN, WE'RE THE BOMB.
>> Jeff: AND THEIR HIERARCHY
WAS CLEARLY ESTABLISHED:
BRENDA, CHASE, NAONKA
AND SASH WERE ON TOP.
>> IT'S A GREAT FEELING TO KNOW
THAT YOU'RE ON THE SIDE
OF THE NUMBERS
AND TO HAVE CONTROL
THIS EARLY IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: ALINA AND KELLY B.
WERE AT THE BOTTOM.
>> I DON'T LIKE YOU.
NEVER HAVE LIKED YOU.
I REALLY DON'T NEED
NO CHARITY CASE ON THE JURY.
>> Jeff: DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE SWITCHING TRIBES.
BUT A SURPRISE SWITCH PUT
OLD AND YOUNG ON BOTH TRIBES.
IT IS LA FLOR WEARING YELLOW
VERSUS ESPADA WEARING BLUE.
AT THE NEW LA FLOR, THE YOUNG
PEOPLE WERE IN CONTROL.
>> WE'RE FIVE AND THREE.
IT LOOKS GOOD.
>> Jeff: AND THEY TOOK JANE
UNDER THEIR WING.
>> I LIKE THESE KIDS!
>> Jeff:
DESPITE SHOWING EVERYONE
HIS HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL,
MARTY ENDED UP AT THE TOP
OF SASH AND BRENDA'S HIT LIST.
>> HE'S COMING INTO OUR HOME
AND ALREADY SETTING UP
LIKE HE'S THE KING.
(\INDISTINCT SHOUT\)
>> Jeff:
FABIO WINS IT FOR LA FLOR!
WHEN THE NEW ESPADA TRIBE
LOST THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
HOLLY JOINED UP
WITH THE YOUNG PEOPLE.
>> I HAVE A BETTER CHANCE
AT GOING FARTHER WITH THE KIDS.
>> Jeff: EVEN THOUGH DAN
WITH HIS BAD KNEE
WAS A PHYSICAL LIABILITY
TO THE TRIBE,
THE YOUNG DECIDED THAT TYRONE
WAS A BIGGER THREAT.
>> TYRONE RIGHT NOW, TYRONE...
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
EVERYONE VOTED AGAINST TYRONE,
EXCEPT FOR YVE, WHO WASN'T TOLD
ABOUT THE YOUNGSTERS' PLANS.
>> TYRONE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: 15 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> TEN DAYS AGO I WAS READY
TO GET OUT OF HERE
AND IF ONE LESSON
I'VE LEARNED OUT HERE IS
QUITTING IS AN EASY WAY OUT.
IF YOU CAN'T HANDLE
THE RAIN, THE WIND,
YOU SHOULD HAVE THOUGHT
OF THAT BEFORE YOU CAME.
YOU SIGNED UP FOR SOMETHING;
SUCK IT UP AND FINISH.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY DO I FEEL LIKE
I WAS LEFT OUT IN THE DARK
WITH YOU AND DANNY SO MUCH?
BECAUSE I WOULD HAVE
BEEN FINE WITH THAT. I MEAN...
>> TYRONE?
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T KNOW
IF DANNY AND I FELT THAT,
BECAUSE YOU HAD
AN ALLIANCE WITH HIM.
>> NO. NO, I DIDN'T.
IT SURPRISES ME THAT HOLLY
BELIEVES THAT TYRONE AND I
WERE AN ALLIANCE, AND THAT'S
WHY THEY COULDN'T TELL ME,
BECAUSE... WE WEREN'T.
IT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH FOR ME,
BUT I'M NOT WALKING OUT OF HERE
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
I WAS KIND OF THINKING YOU AND I
HAD EACH OTHER'S BACKS A BIT
BUT NOW I'M KIND OF FEELING
LIKE A FISH OUT OF WATER.
>> MAYBE WE NEED TO BE
A LITTLE BIT MORE
OPEN AND HONEST WITH EACH OTHER.
>> MM-HMM. WELL...
>> BECAUSE...
BUT DANNY TOLD ME THIS MORNING
THAT HE'S DONE.
HE SAID, "I THINK I'M DONE."
AND I SAID "WHY?"
AND HE SAID
"I CAN'T TAKE THIS WEATHER
AND THIS HUT AND..."
>> I DON'T WANT TO THROW ANYBODY
UNDER THE BUS,
BUT DANNY DOESN'T WANT
TO BE HERE ANYMORE.
SO I'LL TAKE THAT INFORMATION
AND I'LL WORK AROUND THAT.
THAT'S THE GAME OF SURVIVOR.
YOU GOT TO DO WHAT
YOU GOT TO DO TO STAY ALIVE.
>> I THINK THEY ARE STARTING
TO APPRECIATE US.
YOU GET UP,
THE DISHES ARE CLEAN.
IT'S LIKE AT HOME;
MOM CLEANS THE DISHES.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE WENT FROM
BEING, LIKE, IN A SERIOUS DRAMA,
YOU KNOW, BEFORE ARRIVING HERE,
AND I FEEL LIKE I JUST FELL
INTO, LIKE, BILL AND TED'S
EXCELLENT ADVENTURE, YOU KNOW?
>> THE YOUNG TRIBE IS, LIKE, 180
DEGREES FROM WHERE WE CAME FROM.
WE WOULD GET UP, GET WOOD, FISH,
AND THESE GUYS SLEEP ALL DAY.
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT WE'VE BEEN DEALT
A VERY BAD HAND BY COMING ON
TO A TEAM IN MINORITY NUMBERS.
I FEEL LIKE THE YOUNG ONES
BONDED AND BONDED REALLY STRONG.
SO I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE
THEY'D GET RID OF US
IN A HEARTBEAT IF THEY COULD.
>> MORNING, FABIO.
>> MORNING.
>> HOW ARE YOU, MAN?
>> DOING WELL.
>> EVEN THOUGH
WE'RE ALL CALLED LA FLOR,
IT'S STILL YOUNGER TRIBE
AND OLDER TRIBE.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
IT'S YOUNGER TRIBE PLUS JANE.
(\LAUGHS\) I MEAN, LOOK AT JANE.
JANE BLENDS IN RIGHT AWAY
BECAUSE SHE'S JUST
A NATURAL, GENUINE HELPER.
SO IF WE GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I THINK WHAT I WANT TO DO
IS HAVE THREE PEOPLE
VOTE FOR MARTY,
THREE PEOPLE VOTE FOR JILL.
THAT WAY YOU FLUSH OUT THE IDOL
AND... WHATEVER HAPPENS,
ONE OF THEM IS GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
LA FLOR GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW ESPADA TRIBE.
TYRONE VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES, SIR.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THING'S FIRST.
FABIO, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
(\FABIO SIGHS HEAVILY\)
TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NOT
WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING FOR TODAY.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
IS WHAT YOU SEEK.
BECAUSE TONIGHT BOTH TRIBES
ARE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BOTH TRIBES WILL VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT OF THIS GAME.
THERE ARE TWO
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY NECKLACES,
BECAUSE ONE PERSON
FROM EACH TRIBE
WILL WIN IMMUNITY,
WILL BE SAFE AT TONIGHT'S VOTE.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL RACE OUT
INTO AN INDIVIDUAL DIGGING AREA.
YOU'LL USE A PADDLE
TO DIG UP A ROPE RING.
TOSS IT OVER YOUR SHOULDER
INTO A BASKET ON YOUR BACKSIDE,
THEN RACE IT BACK TO THE START.
THE FIRST PERSON TO GET
ALL THREE RINGS WINS IMMUNITY,
IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE,
AND MOVES ON TO THE FINAL ROUND
WHERE YOU WILL COMPETE
FOR TRIBAL REWARD.
IN THE FINAL ROUND,
THE WINNER FROM EACH TRIBE
WILL SQUARE OFF IN A RING TOSS.
FIRST PERSON TO LAND
ALL THREE OF THEIR RINGS
ON THE TARGET
WINS A FEAST FOR THEIR TRIBE.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS:
THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL FIRST
AND VOTE SOMEBODY OUT.
YOU WILL THEN LISTEN IN ON
THE OTHER TRIBE'S TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHILE YOU FEAST
ON CHICKEN AND BEEF KEBOBS.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'LL DRAW
FOR SPOTS, WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, ESPADA LOST
THE ROCK-PAPER-SCISSOR.
THEY'RE GOING FIRST.
ONE PERSON WILL WIN IMMUNITY
FROM THIS TRIBE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
THERE ARE THREE ROPE RINGS
BURIED IN THE SAND.
ONCE YOU FIND ONE,
TOSS IT OVER YOUR SHOULDER,
LAND IT IN THE BASKET
AND TAKE IT TO THE START.
DAN DROPS HIS RING.
ALINA GIVES IT A SHOT.
JUST MISSES.
HOLLY HAS HER FIRST RING.
OFF TO A QUICK START.
ALINA LANDS HER FIRST ONE.
YVE LANDS HER FIRST ONE.
BENRY LANDS HIS FIRST ONE.
HOLLY WITH HER SECOND RING...
AND LANDS IT.
HOLLY NOW IN THE LEAD WITH TWO!
ONE RING LEFT.
DAN STILL STRUGGLING.
ALINA DROPS HER SECOND ONE.
BENRY WITH A NICE TOSS!
BENRY ON THE BOARD
WITH HIS SECOND ONE.
CHASE HAS HIS FIRST!
DAN STILL NOWHERE.
IT IS HOLLY, ALINA AND BENRY
EACH LOOKING
FOR THEIR FINAL RING.
ALINA HAS HERS.
CAN SHE LAND IT?
NO.
HOLLY SCORES HER FINAL RING!
HOLLY MOVING ON TO THE FINAL!
(\APPLAUSE\)
NICELY DONE, HOLLY.
>> GOOD JOB, HOLLY.
>> Jeff: HOLLY,
SAFE FROM THE VOTE TONIGHT.
YOU'LL COMPETE WITH THE WINNER
FROM LA FLOR FOR A TRIBAL FEAST.
ESPADA, HIT YOUR MATS.
LA FLOR, YOU'RE UP.
ALL RIGHT, LA FLOR
NOW SEEKING INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ONE MEMBER OF LA FLOR
WILL TAKE ON HOLLY IN THE FINAL.
SASH HAS HIS FIRST ONE.
BRENDA LANDS HER FIRST ONE.
BRENDA AND SASH
BOTH WITH ONE RING.
FABIO HAS HIS FIRST RING.
MARTY LANDS HIS FIRST ONE!
JILL HAS HER FIRST ONE.
KELLY B. HAS HER FIRST.
EVERYBODY ON THE BOARD
EXCEPT JANE AND PURPLE KELLY.
JANE HAS HER FIRST,
HEADING BACK.
MARTY HAS HIS SECOND.
KELLY B. HAS HER SECOND.
JILL HAS HER SECOND.
WE GOT A RACE!
IT IS JILL, MARTY AND KELLY B.
LOOKING FOR THEIR LAST RINGS.
JILL HAS HER LAST RING.
CAN SHE LAND IT?
NO.
KELLY B. NOW HAS HER THIRD.
JUST MISSES.
JILL WITH ANOTHER SHOT.
JILL LANDS HER FINAL RING!
JILL WINS IMMUNITY!
WILL TAKE ON HOLLY IN THE FINAL
FOR A FEAST.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Jeff:
JILL IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
JILL, YOU WILL TAKE ON HOLLY
FOR A TRIBAL FEAST.
LET'S MOVE.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST TO LAND
ALL THREE RINGS ON A HOOK
WINS FEAST FOR THEIR TRIBE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
TWO PEOPLE
FROM THE ORIGINAL OLDER TRIBE
SQUARING OFF IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> SLOW IT DOWN!
>> Jeff: JILL AND HOLLY.
>> YES!
>> Jeff:
HOLLY LANDS HER FIRST RING.
>> JILL, YOU'VE GOT IT.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> GET IN THE ZONE!
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: JILL LANDS HER FIRST
RING, AND THE SECOND RING.
JILL AND HOLLY BOTH WITH TWO!
ONE RING LEFT.
JILL OR HOLLY
CAN WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
>> GO, JILL!
>> Jeff:
HOLLY JUST MISSES.
JILL WINS FEAST FOR LA FLOR!
>> WE'RE GONNA EAT!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
TONIGHT, LA FLOR,
YOU WILL GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
AND VOTE SOMEBODY OUT,
THEN LISTEN IN
ON ESPADA'S TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND WHILE DOING SO,
YOU WILL FEAST
ON CHICKEN AND BEEF KEBOBS.
LA FLOR, ESPADA, SEE YOU
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> HEY! WINNER, WINNER, WINNER!
IT'S JUST SUCH A GOOD FEELING
TO KNOW THAT
WE'RE GONNA EAT TONIGHT.
>> ...FOR PICKING ME
TO BE ON THIS TEAM.
>> AWESOME.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE...
>> LA FLOR!
>> THE LITTLE
"ONE, TWO, THREE, LA FLOR!"
THAT WAS TOTALLY FAKE.
I MEAN, JILL AND MARTY, COME ON.
YOU COULD SEE THAT
THEY'RE WORKING THEIR MINDS,
THEY'RE WORKING
THEIR OWN LITTLE THING.
YOU JUST FEEL IT.
BUT WORST-CASE SCENARIO
HAPPENED.
JILL WON INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
MARTY HAS THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, SO NOW WE'RE STUCK.
BUT WE WILL SOMEHOW VOTE
SOMEONE OUT THAT WE DON'T WANT.
>> SO WHAT I WAS THINKING--
TELL ME IF YOU WERE THINKING
THE SAME THING--
WE SPLIT THE VOTES,
THREE VOTES... FOR MARTY
AND THREE VOTES FOR KELLY B.
WE TELL KELLY B., THOUGH,
THAT OUR THREE VOTES
ARE GOING FOR...
>> JANE. Yep.
>> JANE.
>> IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
>> THAT EASY.
>> OKAY. COOL.
>> COOL.
>> SINCE JILL WON
THE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY TODAY,
OUR WHOLE STRATEGY
KIND OF CHANGES AT THIS POINT.
SO THE PLAN FOR TONIGHT IS
WE'LL SPLIT THE VOTE
BETWEEN MARTY AND KELLY B.,
AND HOPEFULLY FLUSH THE IDOL.
>> COCONUT!
>> COCONUT! YAY!
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT
THE PLAN THAT WE HAVE IN STORE,
BECAUSE KELLY B. HAS NEVER BEEN
A PART OF OUR ALLIANCE.
YOU KNOW, SHE WAS GUNNING
FOR ME FROM THE START,
PLUS SHE HAS A FAKE LEG.
SO I THINK PEOPLE WOULD GIVE
KELLY B. A MILLION DOLLARS
BECAUSE THEY FEEL BAD FOR HER.
AND, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO HAVE
SOMEONE LIKE THAT AROUND.
>> SO WE NEED TO SPLIT
THREE AND THREE?
>> I MEAN, I LIKE JANE, BUT I
FEEL LIKE OUR HAND WAS FORCED.
I REALLY WANTED
TO SEE JANE AROUND HERE
FOR AS LONG
AS WE COULD KEEP HER,
BUT I'VE BEEN ON THE OUTS
WITH THE LA FLOR GROUP
SO THE BEST THING I CAN DO
IS JUST KIND OF LAY LOW
AND VOTE WITH EVERYONE ELSE.
>> YEAH.
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL
IS NOT GONNA BE EASY,
BECAUSE I HAVE TO, LIKE, MAKE
SURE ALL THESE PIECES ARE SET.
AND YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT FABIO'S GOING TO DO.
I MEAN, HE'S CLUELESS,
SO IT'S GOING TO BE
A LITTLE COMPLICATED.
>> DUDE, I HAVE NOT
TOLD ANYBODY THIS,
NOT EVEN ON MY OWN TRIBE,
BUT I AM...
A GRAND MASTER IN CHESS.
AND HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF GUILLERMO VILA BEFORE?
>> NO, MAN, ALL I'VE HEARD OF
IS BOBBY FISCHER.
>> OKAY, WELL, GUILLERMO VILAS
IS AN ARGENTINE GRAND MASTER.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
I BEAT HIM TWICE.
>> Ha!
>> AND WHEN YOU WANT
TO TALK LATER, MAN...
>> I'M TAKING ORDERS, BRO.
>> IF YOU WANT TO...
IF YOU WANT TO MAKE
THE BIGGEST MOVE OF THIS GAME
EVER IN SURVIVOR,
I'VE GOT IT ALL LAID OUT.
ACTUALLY, I'M NOT
A GRAND MASTER IN CHESS.
AND THE ARGENTINE GRAND MASTER
OF ALL TIME, GUILLERMO VILAS,
HE'S ONE OF THE GREATEST
TENNIS PLAYERS OF ALL TIME
BUT CLEARLY HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH CHESS.
SO I COULD PULL ANYTHING
OUT OF THE '70S ON THESE GUYS
AND THEY WOULDN'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THE BEAUTY IS?
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO MAKE ANY DECISIONS.
>> WHEN MARTY SAYS,
"I AM A GRAND MASTER IN CHESS,"
I'M JUST THINKING...
DUH, LIKE IT MAKES SE...
IT DOES MAKE SENSE, MAN.
HE'S ALWAYS TALKING
ABOUT IT'S A NUMBERS GAME,
AND YOU CAN SEE HIM DOING
ALL THESE NUMBERS IN HIS HEAD,
AND I'M, LIKE, SIGN ME UP.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD DEAL, YOU KNOW?
>> YOU CAN NEVER BE TOO COCKY,
YOU CAN NEVER BE TOO CONFIDENT.
BUT IF I CAN PULL THIS OFF, IT
COULD BE A WHOLE NEW BALL GAME.
>> OH.
>> FIRE THIS BABY UP.
>> I JUST KEPT TOSSING
AND TOSSING AND I WAS, LIKE...
>> OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> I KNOW.
FOR ME TO WIN
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IS GOOD,
BUT AT THE SAME POINT,
THE OTHER TRIBE GETS TO WATCH
OUR TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THEY GET TO EAT IN FRONT OF US,
SO IT'S NOT GONNA BE
A LOT OF FUN.
I JUST KEPT THINKING
ABOUT FOOD AND...
FOR TONIGHT'S VOTE,
I HAVE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
AND THE FOUR YOUNG
ESPADA MEMBERS
DEFINITELY HAVE
THE NUMBERS ADVANTAGE.
SO AT THIS POINT,
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO GO
WITH THE MAJORITY,
AND THE CHOICES TONIGHT
FOR WHO WE CAN VOTE FOR
ARE DAN AND YVE.
SO WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
ON TONIGHT?
I'M GETTING EXHAUSTED
WITH THIS STUFF.
IT'S VERY HARD
BEING HERE AND LIVING HERE.
THE FOOD SITUATION IS BAD,
WEATHER SITUATION IS BAD,
EVERYTHING'S BAD.
AND I DON'T NEED THE MONEY.
I GOT A RANGE ROVER,
I GOT A FERRARI.
I MEAN, WHY IN THE WORLD
AM I DOING THIS?
>> WHEN YOU TALKED TO ME
THIS MORNING,
I GUESS I JUST WANT TO KNOW...
>> THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
>> OKAY. YOU CAN'T QUIT.
I FEEL LIKE DAN
WANTS TO GIVE UP,
BUT NOW HE TOLD ME
HE DOES NOT WANT TO GO HOME.
HE NEEDS TO BE HONEST, BECAUSE
IF HE DOESN'T WANT TO BE HERE,
THERE'S PEOPLE
THAT WANT TO BE HERE.
>> WHY? WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I MEAN, I THINK
IT SHOULD BE YVE THAT GOES.
I'D MUCH RATHER GO
TO THE MERGE WITH DANNY.
I PERSONALLY WANT
TO GET RID OF YVE TONIGHT,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO TAKE HER TO THE MERGE.
SHE'S A SMART PLAYER.
SHE'S HERE TO PLAY
FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS.
DAN, I KNOW FOR A FACT HE'S NOT
A THREAT TO ME WHATSOEVER,
SO IT'S REALLY
A NO-BRAINER TONIGHT FOR ME
TO WANT TO VOTE YVE OUT.
REGARDLESS, US FOUR,
IF WE STICK TOGETHER...
>> FOUR YOUNG.
>> YEAH.
>> I KNOW.
>> WE'RE SET.
>> THE DYNAMIC BETWEEN
THE FOUR ORIGINAL LA FLOR GUYS
IS WE SAY WE TRUST EACH OTHER,
THE ONLY ONE
I REALLY TRULY TRUST IS NAONKA.
BENRY AND ALINA, I THINK
THEY COULD SWITCH LIKE THAT.
BEST SCENARIO FOR ME TONIGHT?
IT COULD POSSIBLY BE
TO KEEP YVE.
>> HERE'S WHAT WE'RE FACING.
IF WE KEEP LOSING,
WE HAVE TO THINK ABOUT THIS.
YVE'S KIND OF CLOSE TO ME,
SO I THINK SHE WOULD TRUST ME.
DAN, THE ONLY THING HE COULD
BE SWAYED POSSIBLY BY BENRY
TO, LIKE, BLIND-SIDE ME
OR SOMETHING.
>> CHASE AND I,
WE ARE REALLY CONFUSED
ON WHO WE WOULD WANT OUT.
IF IT WAS MY CHOICE,
I WOULD CHOOSE DAN TO GO HOME,
BECAUSE THERE'S NO WAY
THAT IF WE CONTINUE KEEPING HIM
IN THIS GAME, WE'RE GONNA WIN.
DAN'S KNEES ARE ABOUT TO CRACK.
HE'S ABOUT TO START WALKING
ON HIS KNEES. (\LAUGHS\)
SOONER OR LATER, HE'S
ABOUT TO BE WALKING ON NUBS.
>> HOLLY WON IMMUNITY,
AND THE YOUNG TRIBE,
THEY'RE PRETTY TIGHT,
SO IT'S ME OR DAN.
AND WE'VE BEEN
TO A LOT OF TRIBALS
WHEN DAN'S NAME GETS WRITTEN
DOWN, BUT HE'S NOT VOTED OUT.
MAYBE HE'S JUST GOT A LITTLE
SOMEONE SITTING ON HIS SHOULDER
WATCHING OUT FOR HIM
THAT I'M HOPING JUMPS SHIP
AND COMES OVER
TO MY SHOULDER TONIGHT.
>> I HAVE TO TELL YOU GIRLS,
I SURE AS HELL
DON'T WANT TO GO HOME, AND I'M
HERE COMMITTED 100% OF THE TIME.
>> WELL, AT THIS POINT,
IT'S STILL A TRIBE GAME,
SO OBVIOUSLY,
WE NEED STRONG PEOPLE.
I THINK IT'S GOT TO BE DAN.
>> HOLLY SAID THIS MORNING
HE SAID "I'M DONE."
AND I'M NOT HERE
TO QUIT HALFWAY.
AND OUT OF THE THREE OF US,
WHEN WE DO MERGE,
I KNOW ALL THREE OF THEM
ON THE OTHER SIDE
MORE INTIMATELY THAN THEY DO.
WHICH WOULD COMPLETELY BENEFIT
YOU TWO... (\INDISTINCT\)
SO ANYWAY,
I JUST WANTED TO SAY THAT, OKAY?
>> NO, I THINK WE WERE
ALREADY ON THE SAME PAGE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YVE CAME UP TO ME AND NAONKA
AND SHE SAID,
"I'M ACTUALLY VALUABLE
TO YOU GUYS
"BECAUSE WHEN
WE GET TO THE MERGE,
I HAVE REALLY GOOD RELATIONSHIPS
WITH THE OLD ESPADA TRIBE."
AND I'M THINKING,
IF WE GET YOU TO THE MERGE
AND YOU HAVE GOOD RELATIONSHIPS,
WHAT MAKES US THINK THAT YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO SWITCH ON US?
CLEARLY, DAN ISN'T
STRONG PHYSICALLY.
BUT THE PROBLEM WITH YVE IS
THAT YVE IS PLAYING REALLY HARD.
SO IN MY HEAD I WENT, WOW,
THAT'S THE PERFECT ARGUMENT
TO GET RID OF HER.
>> 100%.
>> OKAY.
>> I THINK IT'S
ALWAYS MOST IMPORTANT
TO KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG
PHYSICALLY,
BUT, THEN, AT THE SAME TIME,
I THINK THAT YVE MIGHT DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET HERSELF, YOU KNOW,
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
SO SHE COULD BE VERY DANGEROUS.
JUST NEED TO BE SURE THIS IS
THE RIGHT THING FOR US TO DO.
>> YOU GUYS GOT TO TELL ME
WHAT YOU THINK.
I MEAN, THIS IS GETTING
DOWN TO THE WIRE.
>> DO NOT FOLLOW YOUR HEART,
FOLLOW YOUR GUT.
IT WOULD BE DAN, BECAUSE WHAT
IF WE HAVE ANOTHER CHALLENGE
THAT'S SUPER PHYSICAL
AND HIS KNEES HURT?
THEN WHAT?
FIRST CHASE WANTED
TO VOTE FOR DAN.
NOW IT SOUNDS LIKE
CHASE WANTS YVE TAKEN OUT.
OKAY, THAT'S WHAT YOU GUYS
WANT TO DO, TELL ME.
TELL ME RIGHT NOW, IS THAT
WHAT YOU GUYS WANT ME TO DO,
BECAUSE I'LL RIGHT HER NAME DOWN
AND I'LL SMILE IN HER FACE.
THAT'S OUT-WIN.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
COULD HAVE GUESSED IT,
BUT WE ALWAYS WANTED
TO GET MARTY.
>> RIGHT.
>> THEY'VE BEEN MY ENEMIES
FROM DAY ONE.
I'LL DO WHATEVER
Y'ALL WANT ME TO DO, HONEY.
I'M AS THICK AS
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY
WITH THE YOUNGER LA FLOR TRIBE,
SO I HAVE
A LITTLE SMILE ON MY FACE
'CAUSE I BELIEVE
WHAT GOES AROUND COMES AROUND,
BECAUSE THOSE TWO NEVER
PULLED ME INTO THEIR ALLIANCE.
THEY'VE BEEN CONNIVING
SINCE DAY ONE.
SO I HOPE IT GOES
THE WAY BRENDA'S PLANNED IT.
>> NO.
>> WHAT WE'RE THINKING IS,
WE GOT TO FLUSH THE IDOL
AWAY FROM MARTY.
SO WE'RE THINKING
THAT WE SPLIT THE VOTES.
THREE VOTES FOR MARTY...
AND THREE VOTES FOR KELLY B.
>> DO WE WANT TO FLUSH THE IDOL
FROM MARTY?
>> WHY NOT?
I MEAN, IT'S DANGEROUS
TO HAVE HIM HOLD ON TO IT.
MARTY'S A SMART GUY, HE'S GOING
TO USE HIS IDOL TONIGHT, OKAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HE WILL, TRUST ME.
IF YOU VOTE FOR MARTY...
>> I DON'T...
MAN, I LIKE MARTY.
SASH WANTS ME TO VOTE FOR MARTY,
BUT I WANT MARTY
TO STICK AROUND.
HE'S A SMART GUY,
HE'S LET ME IN ON SOME
OF HIS SECRETS, YOU KNOW?
SO I FEEL LIKE
I'M KIND OF IN GOOD WITH HIM.
>> IT'S JUST TOO DANGEROUS
FOR HIM TO HOLD ON
TO THAT IMMUNITY IDOL UNTIL
WHENEVER HE WANTS TO USE IT.
IF EVERYTHING GOES
ACCORDING TO PLAN,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO KILL
A COUPLE BIRDS WITH ONE STONE.
BUT FABIO IS SO UP IN THE AIR
ALL THE TIME,
WHO KNOWS WHICH WAY
THE WIND IS BLOWING
THIS EVENING,
SO SOMETHING COULD GO WRONG.
>> I REALLY WANT
TO STAY IN THE GAME.
ANYTHING I CAN DO.
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME.
I MEAN, ARE YOU...
>> HEY, MAN, YOU KNOW WHAT
THIS GAME'S ALL ABOUT, YOU KNOW?
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT ME
GOING HOME
AND YOU GUYS ARE STRAIGHT UP
AND REALLY HONEST
ABOUT THAT'S THE WAY
THE CHIPS ARE GOING TO FALL,
YOU KNOW,
THEN I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> I THOUGHT WITH FABIO
WE COULD MAYBE SHAKE THINGS UP,
BUT I THINK
IT'S PROBABLY TOO DICEY,
IT'S PROBABLY SAFER
TO GO WITH JANE TONIGHT.
BUYS US A LITTLE TIME.
>> THE VOTE WILL BE DETERMINED
BY WHAT MARTY DOES
WITH THE IDOL.
IF HE PLAYS THE IDOL,
KELLY B.'S GOING HOME.
IF MARTY DOESN'T PLAY THE IDOL,
IT WILL BE A TIE.
AND WE'LL HAVE
TO MAKE A TOUGH DECISION,
BECAUSE MARTY IS
THE NUMBER-ONE ENEMY RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE HE'S A HUGE SCHEMER.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO KEEP
A PISSED-OFF KELLY B.
WHO CAN WIN THE WHOLE THING?
SO ENEMY; KELLY B.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> UH, FABIO
DIDN'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
PUTTING HIS VOTE FOR MARTY.
IT'S A VERY,
VERY CALCULATED DECISION
TO PLAY OR NOT PLAY THE IDOL.
MY GUT IS TELLING ME
THEY WILL VOTE FOR JANE,
SO I'LL HANG ON TO IT.
IT WOULD ONLY BUY ME
ONE MORE TRIBAL COUNCIL ANYWAYS.
BUT IT COULD VERY WELL BE ME
GOING HOME TONIGHT
IF I MAKE THE WRONG DECISION.
>> Jeff:
MARTY, OBVIOUS DISPARITY.
FIVE YOUNG; THREE OLD.
EVEN LOOKING AT THIS GROUP,
YOU AND JILL AND JANE,
YOU KIND OF LOOK
LIKE YOU DON'T MAYBE FIT IN.
>> YEAH,
THINGS CHANGED RADICALLY.
YOU'RE IN ONE POSITION ONE DAY
AND... JUST LIKE THAT,
IT ALL CHANGES.
SO THE IMPORTANT THING IS,
THIS TRIBE IS ALL ABOUT WINNING,
SO IF YOU CONTRIBUTE
TOWARDS THAT
AND DO YOUR WORK AROUND CAMP,
I THINK, YOU KNOW,
THINGS HOPEFULLY GO YOUR WAY.
>> Jeff: SASH,
ON DAY ONE OF THIS NEW TRIBE,
WHAT DID MARTY DO
TO TRY TO MAKE HIMSELF WORTHY?
>> VERY FIRST DAY,
MARTY KIND OF CALLED A MEETING
TO NOT ONLY INTRODUCE HIMSELF
BUT HE ALSO MENTIONED TO US
THAT HE WAS HOLDING ON
TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> Jeff: SO, MARTY,
YOU TOLD EVERYBODY
THAT YOU HAD
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I THOUGHT
TO GET OFF ON THE BEST START
THAT I COULD WITH THIS TRIBE
WAS TO COME CLEAN
AND LET THEM KNOW,
HEY, LISTEN, I HAVE THE IDOL,
I'M GOING TO HANG IT
RIGHT OUT ON THE TREE,
AND BY DOING SO, HOPEFULLY
IT BOUGHT ME SOME GOODWILL
AND SHOWED THEM WHAT KIND
OF GAME I'VE BEEN PLAYING,
WHICH HAS BEEN A REALLY, REALLY
STRAIGHT GAME FROM DAY ONE.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, ON ONE HAND,
THIS IS A GESTURE OF GOODWILL,
"I'M GOING
TO LET YOU KNOW I HAVE IT."
ON THE OTHER HAND, HE'S SAYING,
"WATCH OUT, I GOT IT."
>> TOTALLY. YEAH, DEFINITELY.
AND SO I FEEL LIKE
MAYBE IS HE TRYING
TO MAKE IT LOOK
MORE NOBLE THAN IT REALLY IS.
>> Jeff: SO, MARTY,
NOW YOU HAVE TO FIGURE OUT,
ARE THEY GOING TO GUN FOR ME
AND TRY TO GET ME TO PLAY IT,
OR ARE THEY GOING TO TELL ME I'M
SAFE, HOPING I WON'T PLAY IT,
AND GET RID OF ME
AND THE IDOL IN ONE FELL SWOOP?
>> YEAH. ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T THINK
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT THIS
A LITTLE BIT, JUST A WEE BIT,
OVER THE PAST FEW DAYS?
THIS GAME IS ALSO ABOUT TRUSTING
PEOPLE THAT I'VE TALKED TO,
AS FAR AS "TRUST"
GETS YOU IN THIS GAME,
AND, I DON'T KNOW,
I'M GETTING MIXED VIBES,
AND IT'D BE TERRIBLE
TO GO HOME TONIGHT
WITH AN IDOL IN MY POCKET,
BUT YOU GOT
TO TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS
AND TRY TO STAY TRUE TO THEM.
>> Jeff: KELLY B.,
MARTY SAYS-- AS FAR AS YOU CAN
TRUST SOMEONE IN THIS GAME.
HOW FAR CAN YOU TRUST SOMEONE
IN THIS GAME?
>> I THINK, LIKE HE SAID,
YOU HAVE TO GO
WITH YOUR GUT INSTINCT.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO TELL YOU WHAT THEY NEED TO,
SO I WOULDN'T TRUST
TOO MANY PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: SPEAKING
FOR MARTY OR FOR YOURSELF?
>> I MEAN, FOR ANYONE HERE.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, EVERYONE'S
GOT THEIR OWN INTENTIONS.
>> Jeff: AND SO HOW COMFORTABLE
ARE YOU TONIGHT,
IN TERMS OF TRUSTING
THESE OTHER PEOPLE?
>> I FEEL
PRETTY COMFORTABLE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: JANE, HOW ABOUT YOU?
DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE PART OF THE MAJORITY?
>> I MEAN, THEY MIGHT CONSIDER
ME ONE OF THE "WEAKER PEOPLE,"
AS FAR AS STRENGTH GOES.
>> Jeff: BRENDA,
DOES JANE HAVE REASON TO WORRY?
>> NO. SHE HAS TO WORRY FOR
JILL AND MARTY VOTING HER OUT.
THAT'S THE TRUTH.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> COME ON, MARTY.
>> ME AND JILL ARE TWO,
YOU GUYS ARE FIVE,
SO THAT'S REALLY SWEET OF YOU
TO PUT THAT ON ME.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ME AND JILL,
SO APPRECIATE ALL THAT.
>> BUT WHAT DID YOU
TELL ME TODAY?
>> BUT... THAT'S NOT...
THAT'S NOT WHAT
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU SAID WHAT
SHE HAS TO WORRY ABOUT.
WHAT SHE HAS TO WORRY ABOUT
ARE NUMBERS.
THESE TWO NUMBERS HERE
DON'T ADD UP TO A LOT.
>> FIVE DO. SO YOU'RE WRONG.
>> I KNOW, BUT...
>> NO, I'M JUST SAYING
YOU'RE WRONG.
>> I'M NOT CAMPAIGNING FOR JANE
TO BE OUT; YOU GUYS WERE.
>> I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
I'M JUST SAYING
LA FLOR MADE THE CALL.
I DIDN'T MAKE THAT CALL.
>> BUT YOU DID SAY THAT.
>> SO IF I APPROACHED YOU,
IT WAS TO GET CONSENSUS
WITHIN YOUR TRIBE
TO MAKE SURE THAT
YOU GUYS ARE IN AGREEMENT.
I NEVER OFFERED UP JANE.
>> Jeff: MARTY,
YOU FEELING MORE COMFORTABLE,
LESS COMFORTABLE, SAME AS
YOU WERE WHEN YOU WALKED IN?
>> UH, PROBABLY LESS COMFORTABLE
SIMPLY BECAUSE I TOOK
THESE GUYS AT FACE VALUE
AND I FEEL THERE'S
A LOT OF, UH, DUPLICITY,
BASED ON SOME
OF THE COMMENTS MADE HERE.
I NEVER INITIATED
A VOTE ON JANE.
THAT WOULD BE MORONIC OF ME.
THAT CONNIVING
AND BACKSTABBING KIND OF STUFF
THAT THEY SAID THEY DIDN'T LIKE
MAKES ME FEEL A LITTLE UNEASY,
BECAUSE I MISJUDGED
A LITTLE BIT IN THE BEGINNING,
YOU KNOW, WHAT I WAS SEEING,
SO YEAH, MORE UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> Jeff: WELL, BASED
ON WHAT'S BEEN SAID TONIGHT,
I COULDN'T EVEN GUESS
WHO I THINK IS GOING HOME.
SO LET'S END THE SUSPENSE
AND GET TO THE VOTE
JILL, YOU HAVE
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
I TAKE IT YOU'RE
KEEPING THAT FOR YOURSELF?
CANNOT VOTE FOR JILL.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
JILL, YOU'RE UP.
>> DON'T EVER FLUFF OFF
A SOUTHERN WOMAN.
I AIN'T NO SITTING DUCK, HONEY.
>> YOU'RE THE BLACK WIDOW,
KING COBRA AND BLACK MAMBA
ALL ROLLED INTO ONE.
YOU MAY NOT BE
GOING HOME TONIGHT,
BUT THE LINES HAVE BEEN DRAWN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO
TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES
ARE READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE...
MARTY.
MARTY. TWO VOTES MARTY.
THREE VOTES MARTY.
BRENDA. THREE VOTES MARTY;
ONE VOTE BRENDA.
BRENDA.
TWO VOTES BRENDA.
KELLY B.
THREE VOTES MARTY;
TWO VOTES BRENDA;
ONE VOTE KELLY B.
KELLY B.
THREE VOTES MARTY;
TWO VOTES BRENDA;
TWO VOTES KELLY B;
ONE VOTE LEFT.
WE HAVE A TIE.
MARTY HAS THREE VOTES;
KELLY B. HAS THREE VOTES.
>> Jeff: WE HAVE A TIE.
MARTY HAS THREE VOTES;
KELLY B. HAS THREE VOTES.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
MARTY, KELLY B.,
YOU WILL NOT VOTE.
EVERYBODY ELSE WILL VOTE,
AND YOU'RE VOTING
FOR MARTY OR KELLY B.
JANE, COME GET THE URN.
YOU'RE UP FIRST.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO
TALLY THE VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE...
MARTY.
KELLY B.
ONE VOTE MARTY;
ONE VOTE KELLY B.
KELLY B.
TWO VOTES KELLY B.;
ONE VOTE MARTY.
KELLY B. THAT'S THREE VOTES
KELLY B.; ONE VOTE MARTY.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA...
KELLY B.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
KELLY B., THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
(\THUNDER RUMBLING\)
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU ARE NOW GOING TO LISTEN IN
ON THE TRIBAL COUNCIL OF ESPADA
WHILE YOU FEAST
ON CHICKEN AND BEEF KEBOBS.
GO AHEAD AND MOVE ACROSS.
>> GOING INTO TONIGHT,
I WAS PRETTY SURE
THAT THERE WAS CONSENSUS
ON THE TRIBE THAT WE WERE,
YOU KNOW, GOING TO KEEP
THE YOUNG PEOPLE TOGETHER,
AND SO TO BE SINGLED OUT,
FOR WHATEVER REASON,
YOU KNOW,
I JUST NEVER GOT A VIBE
THAT, LIKE,
I DID SOMETHING WRONG.
I MEAN, I'M SURPRISED
BY THE DECISION TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
ESPADA FOR THEIR TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LA FLOR JUST FINISHED
THEIR TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THEY VOTED OUT KELLY B.
THEY'RE NOW GOING
TO ENJOY A MEAL
WHILE THEY LISTEN IN
ON YOUR TRIBAL.
LA FLOR, START EATING.
>> Jeff: CHASE,
HARD TO WATCH THAT?
>> IT'S VERY HARD TO WATCH THAT.
>> Jeff: NAONKA,
YOU'RE NOT EVEN LOOKING.
>> I CAN'T LOOK.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT MYSELF
BY LOOKING OVER THERE.
>> Jeff: HOW IS IT, FABIO?
>> (\LAUGHING\):
SO GOOD, MAN, SO GOOD.
>> YOU WOULD ASK HIM, HUH?
>> Jeff: HOLLY,
TOUGH TO SIT HERE
HAVING TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT
WHILE WATCHING
ANOTHER TRIBE FEAST?
>> IT'S VERY HARD.
I'D HAVE RATHER GIVEN UP
MY INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
FOR THE TRIBE TO BE SITTING
OVER THERE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff:
DAN, YOU CAN HEAR THE ICE CUBES
PLUNKING IN THE GLASSES.
>> IF IT'S NOT A MARTINI,
IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME.
(\LAUGHTER\)
>> Jeff: WHAT DOES BOTHER YOU?
>> NOTHING.
IF THINGS BOTHERED ME,
I WOULDN'T BE HERE.
>> Jeff:
GETTING VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME,
WILL THAT BOTHER YOU
IF IT HAPPENS?
>> THAT WOULD BOTHER ME, YES.
>> Jeff: SO, YVE, WHY WOULD
HE SAY NOTHING BOTHERS HIM?
>> BECAUSE THAT
WAS THE ANSWER HE GAVE YOU.
BUT WHEN YOU HEAR HIM
AROUND CAMP
CONSTANTLY COMPLAINING
ABOUT THE RAIN, THE COLD--
EVERY DAY
SOMETHING IS AGITATING HIM
TO THE BRINK
OF ALMOST NOT WANTING TO STAY.
>> Jeff: DAN, HAVE YOU WANTED
TO QUIT THIS GAME?
>> NO. I MEAN, THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN I DO COMPLAIN.
YOU KNOW, I'M OUT THERE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
WITH THE FIRE--
THAT'S NOT ENJOYABLE.
SO, UH, SURE I SAY THINGS.
>> BUT IT'S JUST CONSISTENT,
AND WE NEED MORE POSITIVE ENERGY
AND COMMITMENT 100% OF THE TIME.
>> Jeff: BENRY,
IS IT A FAIR STATEMENT
TO SAY THAT DAN IS
A LIABILITY AT CHALLENGES?
>> YEAH. I MEAN,
IT'S FAIR TO SAY.
THERE ARE DEFINITELY
SOME OF US ON THIS TRIBE
THAT ARE A LITTLE MORE PHYSICAL
AND DOING WELL
IN THESE CHALLENGES.
BUT I WOULDN'T SAY
HE'S INCOMPETENT,
YOU KNOW, BY ANY MEANS.
>> Jeff: DAN, IS IT FAIR TO SAY,
WHEN IT COMES TO CHALLENGES
YOU'RE A BIT OF A LIABILITY?
>> I WOULD SAY
CERTAIN CHALLENGES.
BUT I'M STILL OUT THERE.
I'M DOING WHATEVER I HAVE TO DO.
>> Jeff: YVE,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT LOGIC?
"I'LL GIVE YOU WHAT I HAVE.
SOMETIMES I CAN'T GIVE YOU
WHAT YOU NEED."
>> I GIVE WHAT I HAVE
100% OF THE TIME AS WELL,
BUT I DON'T FEEL
I'M A LIABILITY.
>> Jeff: DO YOU THINK
DANIEL'S A LIABILITY?
>> I DO. I MEAN,
I LOVE THE GUY, I DO, BUT...
>> REALLY SOUNDS IT.
THAT'S A HECK OF A WAY
OF SAYING YOU LOVE SOMEBODY.
>> Jeff: DO YOU FEEL
ANIMOSITY FROM YVE?
>> ABSOLUTELY. AND I THINK
THAT SHE FEELS TONIGHT
MIGHT NOT BE
A GOOD NIGHT FOR HER.
>> Jeff: FAIR STATEMENT, YVE...
>> FAIR STATEMENT,
FAIR STATEMENT. I DO.
I FEEL LIKE MY HEAD'S
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> Jeff: DAN, TELL ME WHY
THEY SHOULD GET RID OF YVE.
>> WELL, I GUESS YOU COULD
HEAR IT IN YVE'S VOICE.
SHE'S PRETTY ARROGANT.
>> ARROGANT?
WHAT ABOUT ME'S ARROGANT?
I DON'T TALK ABOUT MY FERRARIS
AND MY SIX CARS
AND MY THREE HOMES.
>> I DO.
>> I KNOW.
BUT WHAT ABOUT ME IS ARROGANT?
>> IT'S JUST YOUR OVERALL...
JUST YOUR OVERALL ATTITUDE.
>> Jeff: ALINA,
IS IT A FAIR STATEMENT
TO SAY THAT IT APPEARS TO BE
DAN OR YVE THAT'S GOING HOME?
>> YEAH. I MEAN, IT'S BEEN
GOING AROUND CAMP ALL DAY,
DO WE WANT TO KEEP SOMEBODY
WHO MAY BE A LIABILITY FOR US
BUT ISN'T GOING TO BE SOMEBODY
WHO'S A SUPER COMPETITOR,
OR DO WE WANT TO KEEP SOMEBODY
WHO IS PLAYING REALLY HARD
AND JUST MAKES
MORE COMPETITION FOR YOU?
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
IT IS TIME TO GET TO THE VOTE,
WHICH MEANS, LA FLOR,
IT'S TIME FOR YOU GUYS TO GO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HOLLY,
YOU HAVE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
I ASSUME YOU'RE KEEPING THAT
FOR YOURSELF.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: YOU CANNOT VOTE
FOR HOLLY.
ANYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DAN, YOU'RE UP.
>> WHAT CAN I SAY, DAN?
LOOKS LIKE
IT'S EITHER ME OR YOU,
AND I'D MUCH RATHER IT BE YOU.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO
TALLY THE VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE: YVE.
DAN. ONE VOTE YVE;
ONE VOTE DAN.
YVE. THAT'S TWO VOTES YVE;
YVE. THAT'S THREE VOTES YVE;
ONE VOTE DAN.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT
OF SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA...
YVE. THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
YVE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, BASED ON TONIGHT'S VOTE,
IT WOULD SEEM
THIS IS ONE UNIFIED TRIBE.
BASED ON WHAT I HEARD,
NOT SO SURE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP. GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR.
>> WHY DON'T I GO UP TO MARTY
AND TELL HIM,
"GIVE ME THE IDOL."
>> Jeff: SASH REVEALS
A CRAFTY SIDE.
>> YOU HAND THE IDOL OVER.
>> Jeff: JANE REVEALS
A SNEAKY SIDE.
>> I WANT ME A FISH.
I'M NOT GONNA TAKE HIM
BACK TO CAMP.
BON APPETIT.
>> Jeff: AND FABIO REVEALS...
FABIO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
RIGHT NOW?
...TOO MUCH INFORMATION.
>> I'M USING THE RESTROOM.
>> Jeff: IN THE POOL?
>> IT'S FRUSTRATING TO BE
OUT OF THIS GAME AT THIS POINT.
DISAPPOINTED IN MYSELF.
IT'S NOT WHAT I CAME HERE TO DO.
DID I INTEND TO WIN?
THAT WAS MY GOAL,
BUT I CERTAINLY DIDN'T HAVE
ANY ANTICIPATION OF GOING OUT
SO EARLY IN THE GAME.
I DO THINK IT WAS A MISTAKE
TO LET ME GO.
PERHAPS THEY HAVE REASONS
FOR LETTING ME GO
THAT I'M CLEARLY NOT AWARE OF.