>> Jeff:
PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR,
DURING THE PAST FOUR WEEKS,
THESE CASTAWAYS
HAVE ENDURED SEVERE STORMS
THAT NEARLY WASHED
AWAY THEIR CAMP.
>> HAVING THREE NIGHTS
OF HORRIBLE RAIN IS MISERABLE.
>> Jeff: AND AN ACCIDENTAL FIRE
THAT BURNED UP THEIR FOOD.
>> OH MY GOD!
>> Jeff: A MONTH IN NICARAGUA
HAD MADE ONE THING CLEAR--
THIS IS NO PLACE FOR THE WEAK.
BACK ON DAY FIVE,
HOLLY MELTED DOWN
AND WANTED TO QUIT.
>> I CAN'T DO IT.
>> Jeff: BUT AFTER A PEP TALK
FROM COACH JIMMIE JOHNSON...
>> WE REALLY DO NEED YOU.
>> Jeff: ...SHE STAGED
A COMPLETE TURNAROUND
AND FORGED A STRONG ALLIANCE
WITH CHASE AND JANE.
>> ONE LESSON
I'VE LEARNED OUT HERE
IS QUITTING IS AN EASY WAY OUT.
YOU SIGNED UP FOR SOMETHING.
SUCK IT UP AND FINISH.
>> Jeff: ON DAY 13,
RAIN AND BITTER COLD
MADE NAONKA WANT TO BAIL,
BUT KIND WORDS FROM CHASE
WARMED HER UP
AND KEPT HER IN THE GAME.
>> WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL MAKE IT THROUGH THIS.
THIS AIN'T NOTHING.
>> Jeff: ON DAY 15,
PURPLE KELLY HIT THE WALL.
>> I HAVEN'T REALLY BEEN,
LIKE, WARM.
LIKE EVERY NIGHT
HAS BEEN FREEZING.
IT'S KILLING ME OUT HERE.
I JUST WANT TO QUIT.
>> Jeff: BUT SHE STAYED
BECAUSE HE WAS BLINDLY OBEDIENT
TO TRIBE LEADERS BRENDA
AND SASH.
>> WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
IT'S REALLY WHATEVER SASH
AND I WANT.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL,
HOLLY AND JANE LED A CONSPIRACY
TO TAKE BRENDA OUT.
SO SHE TRIED TO DIVERT ATTENTION
TO NAONKA.
>> IT WAS NAONKA WANTING
TO JUMP SHIP.
>> Jeff: BRENDA'S
LONG-TIME ALLY, SASH,
COULD HAVE SAVED HER
IF HE COUGHED UP
HIS HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
BUT HE DIDN'T.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT,
AND THE THIRD MEMBER
OF OUR JURY, BRENDA.
>> BRENDA WAS VOTED OUT
AND PURPLE KELLY
WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO DIDN'T SEE IT COMING.
NINE ARE LEFT,
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> I CAN'T SEE A THING.
I'M HITTING A BRANCH.
>> IT'S A LITTLE FURTHER.
>> SASH.
>> THANKS, BUDDY.
>> YEP.
>> TONIGHT WAS WILD.
>> IT WAS TOO WILD.
>> LIKE, I DON'T...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND AT ALL
WHAT IS GOING ON.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT...
>> WHO DID YOU END UP
VOTING FOR?
>> BRENDA.
>> OH, YOU DID?
>> YEAH, DID YOU HEAR
ALL SHE WAS TALKING ABOUT ME?
>> SHE REALLY CALLED YOU
OUT ON EVERYTHING.
BRENDA LEAVING THE GAME, LIKE,
COMPLETELY SCREWED ME OVER.
I WAS JUST COMPLETELY LEFT
IN THE DARK,
AND IT'S, LIKE,
THANK GOD I HAVEN'T BEEN LEFT
IN THE DARK FOR 28 DAYS
BECAUSE I'D BE GOING... NUTS.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT TO EXPECT FROM HERE ON OUT.
HAVING NAONKA, CHASE,
AND SASH TURN ON ME
PUT ME AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE TOTEM POLE
OF ANY ALLIANCE
I WERE TO BE A PART OF.
>> SO I FEEL WE SENT THE RIGHT
PERSON HOME TONIGHT.
>> YEAH, ME, TOO.
>> I THINK WHAT SHE SAW
IS THAT YOU HAD FLIPPED,
AND SHE KNEW YOU WERE
GETTING INFORMATION OUT OF HER
AND COMING BACK AND TELLING US.
>> UH-HUH.
>> BUT THAT MAKES ME
TRUST YOU MORE.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHEN YOU TELL ME STUFF
LIKE THAT.
SO DON'T THINK IT'S GOING
TO WORK AGAINST YOU.
>> OKAY.
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL,
BRENDA SHOWED HER ASS.
SHE LITERALLY THREW ME
UNDER THE BUS
AND RAN OVER ME FORWARD
AND BACKWARDS
AND THEN HAD THE NERVE
TO WRITE MY NAME DOWN.
>> SO DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> OKAY. DO I LOOK LIKE
BOO BOO THE FOOL?
YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE
MAKING ME LOOK BAD?
BITCH, YOU MADE ME LOOK GOOD.
>> I AIN'T GONNA WORRY.
WHAT BRENDA SAID
ABOUT YOU TONIGHT
WAS IN ONE EAR
AND OUT THE OTHER.
>> OKAY.
>> SO DON'T PANIC.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND I'M NOT AFRAID OF NOTHING.
NOBODY INTIMIDATES ME HERE.
IF ANYTHING I INTIMIDATE THEM
BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE AFRAID
OF THE WORDS THAT I'LL USE
WHEN I GO OFF ON THEM.
WHATEVER, SHE'S GONE.
>> SO, AT THIS POINT, I MEAN,
IF YOU, ME, HOLLY AND JANE
STICK TOGETHER...
>> YEAH, WE HAVE TO.
>> SO, TWO PEOPLE ON THE OUTS
IS PURPLE AND SASH.
>> YEAH.
>> THE PROBLEM IS GONNA BE
GETTING OUT SASH,
'CAUSE HE HAS AN IDOL.
>> SO YOU JUST BLINDSIDE HIM.
>> NOW MY FOUR ALLIANCE
IS HOLLY, JANE, AND NAONKA.
AND HOPEFULLY,
I GO THROUGH SASH,
PURPLE KELLY AND FABIO,
BUT THIS GAME AIN'T SEEMED
TO WORK LIKE THAT SO FAR,
SO I'M EXPECTING SOMETHING
TO CHANGE, I'M SURE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> LOOK AT THAT, BRO.
>> LOOK AT THAT MUD.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
>> WE WOKE UP
AND RAIN HAD SET IN.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST A DELUGE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> AND WHAT WAS
OUR NICE LITTLE POND
IS NOW A RAGING RIVER.
>> SEE THAT BIG LOG GOING DOWN?
>> IT'S LIKE CLASS-3 RAPIDS.
>> HOPEFULLY,
THIS IS GOING TO LET UP
BECAUSE THIS MAKES
CAMP LIFE MISERABLE.
>> THIS IS INSANE.
AS IT RAINS AND IT POURS,
IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE CRAP.
I AM ANEMIC, SO WHEN I GET COLD,
MY JOINTS,
THEY GET STUCK AND THEY HURT.
THEY, LIKE, THEY FREEZE.
IT HURTS.
IT'S THE END OF THE GAME,
AND I'M-- I'M JUST TRYING,
I'M TRYING, I'M TRYING.
>> THERE'S NO WAY
PEOPLE UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU GO THROUGH OUT HERE.
>> HERE IT COMES, BABY.
>> THERE'S JUST ONLY
SO MUCH I CAN DO.
I KEEP TRYING TO TELL MYSELF
ANYTHING I CAN JUST
TO STAY IN THE GAME,
JUST GET THROUGH IT DAY BY DAY.
I JUST DON'T KNOW,
LIKE, PHYSICALLY,
HOW MUCH LONGER
I CAN PUT UP WITH THIS.
>> IT'S REALLY AFFECTING YOU,
HUH?
>> IT'S JUST, LIKE, WEIRD, TOO,
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE I NEVER FELT
ANYTHING LIKE THIS, YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I DON'T WANT TO JUST,
LIKE, GIVE UP.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
IT'S, LIKE,
HOW MUCH CAN I REALLY TAKE?
IT'S LIKE I MADE IT SO FAR
AND I JUST WANT TO, LIKE,
TRY AND STICK IN THERE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
>> THE ELEMENTS ARE DEFINITELY
A FACTOR OUT HERE.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES IT WILL RAIN
FOR FOUR OR FIVE HOURS,
YOU KNOW.
OUR TARP WAS OBVIOUSLY BURNED.
IT WAS COMING IN THE FRONT.
IT WAS COLD.
YOU JUST HAVE TO,
YOU HAVE TO, LIKE,
FIND A MENTAL HAPPY PLACE
AND YOU'VE JUST GOT TO SAY,
"THIS IS TEMPORARY.
I CAN DEAL WITH IT."
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU GUYS?
THIS IS ALL GOING TO MAKE US
STRONGER PEOPLE.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU OKAY, NAY?
>> MY ASS HURTS.
>> OH, BABY!
>> FRANKLY, YOU KNOW,
I DON'T REALLY CARE.
I'D LOVE FOR NAONKA
AND PURPLE KELLY TO WALK OUT.
>> YEAH, ME, TOO.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE COULD
BE LOSING A COUPLE.
AND I'M SITTING BACK, LIKE, HEY,
WE'RE IN THE FREAKING
RAIN FOREST.
I MEAN, COME ON, YOU KNOW.
FOUR HOURS OF RAIN,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO QUIT
THAT EASILY.
YOU DON'T BELONG HERE.
SO, YOU KNOW,
GO AHEAD AND PACK YOUR BAGS
AND GET OUT, FOR ALL I CARE.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU SAID YOU WERE READY TO QUIT.
>> WELL,
YOU ALREADY KNOW
SINCE THE SWITCH HAPPENED,
HOW I WAS FEEL WITH THE WEATHER
AND I WANTED TO LEAVE.
BUT YOU TALKED ME OUT OF IT,
AND YOU WAS LIKE,
YOU GOTTA STAY.
WE SAID OUR PRAYERS.
WE DID ALL OF THAT.
MY HEART'S NOT IN THE GAME
LIKE IT SHOULD BE.
AND I'VE HAD THIS KEY FOREVER.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU KNOW,
AND I'M GOING TO GIVE IT TO YOU
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY BOY.
I WOULDN'T GIVE IT
TO NOBODY ELSE.
SO, ANYWAY, I'M GOING
TO GIVE YOU THE KEY TO THE GAME.
THERE'S THE IDOL.
>> THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE SEEN IT.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH.
I HAVEN'T SEEN IT YET.
I KNEW IT WAS A KEY,
BUT I AIN'T SEEN IT.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, JUST KNOW, I MEAN,
I APPRECIATE THE HELL
OUT OF THIS.
NAONKA GAVE ME IDOL
BECAUSE SHE THINKS
I CAN DO WELL WITH IT, I GUESS,
AND HOPEFULLY IT WILL
HELP ME OUT IN THE LONG RUN.
>> YOU JUST GOT
TO WORK YOUR MAGIC.
NOW YOU GOT
TO TURN YOUR SWAG ON.
>> IF NAONKA DOESN'T QUIT,
THEN I'M STILL NOT GOING
TO GIVE HER THE IDOL BACK.
>> DON'T GET SCATTER BRAINED.
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU AND I AND SASH AND CHASE
NEED TO STICK TOGETHER.
>> OH, HELL, YEAH.
>> YEAH, TOP FOUR, BABY.
THAT'S A NO-BRAINER.
>> BECAUSE IF KELLY DECIDES
TO STAY IN...
>> NO, SHE'S GOING THROUGH...
>> SHE MIGHT CHANGE HER MIND
AFTER SHE GETS WARM.
BUT SEE, RIGHT NOW,
I THINK SASH IS GOING
TO STAY WITH US,
BUT THEN YOU'VE GOT DANNY...
>> THERE'S THREE OF THEM.
>> THERE'S ONLY THREE OF THEM?
>> YEAH, DANNY, BENRY,
AND FABIO.
>> OH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
IF PURPLE KELLY AND NAONKA
DECIDE TO LEAVE,
I THINK WE STILL HAVE
A FOUR-WAY ALLIANCE
BETWEEN SASH, HOLLY,
CHASE AND ME,
SO THAT ONLY LEAVES
THE OTHER THREE PEOPLE
ON THEIR OWN,
AND IF WE KEEP FOUR STRONG,
WE CAN VOTE THEM OUT.
>> HERE'S MY THING.
US THREE AND JANE.
>> RIGHT.
>> YEAH
>> THIS IS NO...
I'M NOT FLOPPING.
>> YOU DON'T... YOU CAN'T!
>> OBVIOUSLY NOT.
I'D BE STUPID TO.
>> BECAUSE YOU LEARNED
FROM THE FIRST TIME.
LOOK IF YOU HAD FLOPPED
WITH BRENDA,
YOU'D BE THE NEXT ONE TO GO.
>> I KNOW.
I DO NOT TRUST CHASE,
HOLLY AND JANE
AS MUCH AS I DO PURPLE KELLY
AND NAONKA
BECAUSE THEY'RE THE TWO
THAT I'M CLOSEST WITH
AT LIBERTAD.
SO THE PERSON THAT DOES NOT
BENEFIT THE MOST IS ME.
IT CROSSED MY MIND TO TEAM UP
WITH BENRY, FABIO, AND DAN,
BUT I ABSOLUTE WISH NAONKA
AND PURPLE KELLY WOULD STAY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU WILL BE DIVIDED
INTO TWO TEAMS.
YOU'LL BE TETHERED TOGETHER.
EACH TEAM WILL HAVE
AN EIGHT-FOOT, STUFFED DUMMY
NAMED GULLIVER TIED TO A TABLE.
ON MY GO,
YOU WILL RACE TO UNTIE GULLIVER,
AND PICK HIM UP AND CARRY HIM
OVER A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
IF YOU DROP GULLIVER,
YOU HAVE TO GO BACK
TO THE PREVIOUS OBSTACLE.
FIRST TEAM TO CROSS
THE FINISH LINE
WITH GULLIVER WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TEAM
WILL LEAVE HERE
AND BE TAKEN
TO OUR SURVIVOR CINEMA
WHERE YOU WILL ENJOY
A MOVIE PREMIERE.
IT'S A SNEAK PEEK OF A MOVIE
CALLED GULLIVER'S TRAVELS,
NOT YET BEEN RELEASED
STARRING JACK BLACK
AND JASON SIEGEL.
WHILE YOU ARE WATCHING
THIS MOVIE,
YOU WILL ENJOY MOVIE FOOD,
NACHOS, HOT DOGS,
POPCORN AND LOTS
AND LOTS OF CANDY.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: NOW, THERE'S A THEME
TO THIS MOVIE.
THE THEME IS IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW BIG YOU ARE ON THE OUTSIDE.
IT MATTERS HOW BIG YOU ARE
ON THE INSIDE.
YOU GUYS HAVE SURVIVED 28 DAYS.
YOUR ABILITY TO DRAW FROM WITHIN
WILL BE WHAT GETS YOU
THROUGH THESE LAST 11,
AND WILL HELP YOU WIN
TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> EVERY TIME WE GO
TO CHALLENGE,
I'M NOT GOING
TO JUST BE MEDIOCRE
BECAUSE I'M READY TO GO.
I'M STILL GOING TO GO 100%.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET
MY TEAM DOWN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING
TO DO A SCHOOL YARD PICK
TO GET OUR TEAMS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT,
AFTER THE SCHOOL YARD PICK,
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
FOR YELLOW, FABIO, SASH,
JANE, PURPLE KELLY.
FOR BLUE WE HAVE HOLLY,
NAONKA, CHASE, AND BENRY.
DAN WAS NOT SELECTED.
HE AWAITS YOU AT THE FINISH.
DAN HAS OPTED
TO BACK THE BLUE TEAM.
IF THE BLUE TEAM WINS,
DAN WILL JOIN YOU ON REWARD.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> I GOT THIS ONE.
>> Jeff: FIRST THING
YOU HAVE TO DO
IS GET GULLIVER UNTIED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: RESCUE THIS
8-FOOT DUMMY.
>> NO, DON'T DO THAT ONE, KELLY.
NO, I'M ALREADY UNTYING IT.
>> Jeff: YELLOW TEAM
ALREADY HAVING
SOME COMMUNICATION PROBLEMS.
>> OKAY, I GOT THE FEET.
>> Jeff: HOLLY, NAONKA, CHASE
AND BENRY DOING A GREAT JOB.
>> YOU GUYS GOT IT?
>> WE'RE GOOD OVER HERE.
>> HEADS UP.
>> Jeff: BLUE TEAM
WITH A BIT OF A LEAD RIGHT NOW.
NAONKA NOT MESSING AROUND.
SHE IS UP ON THAT TABLE.
BLUE TEAM LOOKING VERY GOOD.
>> NO, NO, NO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT ONE.
>> Jeff: YELLOW TEAM NOW
PICKING UP THE PACE.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
>> WE'VE GOT ONE MORE.
THAT'S ONLY ONE.
THAT'S THE ONLY ONE
WE'VE GOT LEFT.
>> Jeff: YELLOW TEAM NOW
HAS THEIR DUMMY RELEASED.
>> I CAN'T GET THE LAST ONE.
I CAN'T GET THIS ONE.
>> Jeff: YELLOW TEAM PICKS UP
THEIR GULLIVER AND HEADING OUT.
EIGHT FEET AND VERY HEAVY.
>> WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: BLUE TEAM
HAS THEIR GULLIVER.
THEY'RE FREE.
>> TAKE OUR TIME.
>> I GOT HIM, I GOT HIM!
>> Jeff: BOTH TEAMS HEADING OUT
THROUGH THE MUD.
>> PUT HIS HEAD UP.
>> PUT HIS LEG OVER, JANE.
>> Jeff: BOTH TEAMS
ATTACKING THAT FIRST WALL.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
>> COME ON, COME ON, PULL HIM!
>> Jeff: BOTH TEAMS GREAT EFFORT
ON DAY 28.
NOBODY GIVING UP.
EVERYBODY DIGGING DEEP.
>> CHASE, HELP ME HOLD HIM.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN'T
TOSS HIM OVER.
YOU'VE GOT TO CARRY HIM,
AND THAT'S WHERE
IT GETS DIFFICULT.
GULLIVER WEIGHS A LOT.
>> HOLD HIM, BENRY.
>> I GOT HIM.
>> GOT HIM?
>> Jeff: WE ARE NECK AND NECK.
BOTH TEAMS
OVER THE FIRST OBSTACLE
AT THE SAME TIME.
>> GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> HIS LEG IS CAUGHT!
>> I GOT HIM.
>> RUN, GUYS.
WE GOT IT.
>> JUST SET HIM ON THE ROPES.
>> Jeff: YELLOW IS HERE FIRST,
BUT BLUE SNEAKING AHEAD OF THEM,
BENRY NOT WASTING ANY TIME.
BLUE HAS JUST TAKEN OVER YELLOW.
JANE GETTING STUCK.
PURPLE KELLY GETTING STUCK.
YELLOW NOW BACK OUT FIGHTING
FOR THE LEAD.
THIS IS WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT,
RIGHT HERE!
>> COME ON KELLY!
>> Jeff: 28 DAYS IN,
AND EVERYBODY STILL FIGHTING.
NOBODY GIVING UP.
STILL NECK AND NECK.
THROUGH THE ROPES.
THROUGH THE HAY.
>> HEAD'S STUCK WITH MY ARM.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: YELLOW IN THE LEAD.
THEY'RE LITERALLY DRAGGING JANE.
BLUE RIGHT BEHIND.
WE'VE GOT A RACE.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> YOU FIRST.
>> Jeff: IT IS COMING DOWN
TO ONE FINAL OBSTACLE.
>> YOU GUYS YOU HAVE TO GO
OVER AND UNDER.
>> Jeff: FABIO PULLING
FOR YELLOW.
BENRY PULLING FOR BLUE.
THIS IS GOING TO COME DOWN
TO A CLOSE FINISH.
YELLOW WITH A SLIGHT LEAD.
>> COME ON, BEN, PULL HIM!
>> Jeff: BENRY PULLING FOR BLUE.
CHASE SHOVING GULLIVER THROUGH.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT'S IT CAUGHT ON, GUYS?
>> GO!
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: BLUE NOW IN THE LEAD.
IT'S BEEN BACK AND FORTH
THE WHOLE CHALLENGE.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
YOU GOT HIM!
COME ON, GUYS!
>> PUSH!
>> WHAT'S HE STUCK ON?
>> Jeff: BLUE HAS THE HEAD
OUT NOW.
LET'S GO, YELLOW!
DON'T GIVE UP!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: YELLOW, YOU NEED
TO DIG IT RIGHT NOW!
>> TWIST HIM AROUND, GUYS.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH!
GET HIS ASS THROUGH, COME ON.
>> MOVE THE ROPES ASIDE.
>> Jeff: BLUE HAS HALF
THE BODY THROUGH.
NAONKA TAKES A HARD FALL,
BUT IT'S GOING TO BE WORTH IT
AS THE BLUE TEAM WINS REWARD!
>> YAY!
>> WE CAN'T LOOK BACK ON IT.
>> SHOULD WE ASK THEM
IF WE CAN EAT THE CHICKEN?
>> WHO GIVES A FLYING...
THEY'RE EATING TONIGHT.
>> THAT TOOK EVERYTHING IN ME.
>> I JUST WANT A HOT DOG.
THAT'S ALL I WANT IS A HOT DOG.
>> Jeff: BLUE TEAM,
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: NICE REWARD COMING.
DAN, YOU PICKED
THE RIGHT TEAM TO BACK.
NO EFFORT.
YOU GET ALL THE REWARD.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE HERE.
YOU'LL BE TAKEN
TO OUR SURVIVOR CINEMA.
YOU'LL ENJOY A SCREENING,
A SNEAK PEEK
OF GULLIVER'S TRAVELS,
NACHOS, HOT DOGS,
POPCORN,
AND ALL THE CANDY YOU CAN EAT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> JEFF, CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
>> Jeff: YES.
>> I'VE GIVEN THIS GAME 110%.
THIS LAST CHALLENGE,
I GAVE EVERY LAST BIT
OF EVERYTHING THAT I HAD.
AND MY BODY IS JUST WEARING DOWN
AND IT'S TEARING DOWN,
AND THIS WILL BE MY LAST DAY,
AND I WANTED TO GO OUT
WITH A BANG
WITH MY WINNING TEAM.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE QUITTING.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ANYBODY ELSE HERE WANT
TO QUIT?
>> I...
28 DAYS,
IT'S BEEN 28 DAYS
OF AN ADVENTURE, BUT...
>> Jeff: YOU'RE QUITTING, TOO?
>> ONE MORE DAY OFF A COUPLE
OF SPOONS OF RICE
PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY
IS EXHAUSTING.
AND A COUPLE OF HOURS A SLEEP...
THIS IS MY LAST DAY.
>> Jeff: NAONKA, YOU'VE GOT
11 DAYS LEFT.
YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE A QUITTER.
>> I'M NOT A QUITTER.
I GUESS I COULD SAY, ULTIMATELY,
THIS IS MY FIRST TIME QUITTING,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I GOT TO LISTEN TO MY BODY.
AND I'M CONTENT
WITH THE DECISION.
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY,
HOW ABOUT YOU?
YOUNGEST PERSON OUT HERE.
YOU'VE DONE AN AMAZING JOB.
YOU'RE GOING TO WALK AWAY?
>> IT'S CRAZY,
BUT AFTER THE FIRST NIGHT,
I CAN'T BELIEVE I LASTED
27 MORE DAYS AFTER THAT.
THAT WAS INSANE.
AND I HAD INTEGRITY
THE WHOLE TIME.
SO...
I'M GOOD.
>> Jeff: WELL, I'M NOT GOOD.
NAONKA, YOU HAVE DONE THINGS
OUT HERE
THAT YOU HAVE REGRETTED
DAYS LATER,
LIKE STEALING FOOD.
PURPLE KELLY,
YOU JUST SAID IT YOURSELF,
YOU WANTED TO QUIT EARLY ON,
BUT YOU DIDN'T.
SO I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU GUYS
THE THIS AFTERNOON
TO THINK ABOUT IT,
AND WE'RE GOING TO MEET
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
AND IF AFTER THINKING ABOUT IT,
YOU STILL WANT TO WALK AWAY
ON DAY 28
AND GIVE UP A SHOT
AT A MILLION BUCKS, THEN, FINE.
I'M SURE EVERYBODY ELSE HERE
WOULD LOVE IT.
SOUND GOOD?
>> IT DOES.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE THIS CLOSE TO
BEING ABLE TO SAY, "I DID IT."
AND YOU'RE THIS CLOSE
TO BEING ONE OF THOSE OTHERS,
THE QUITTERS,
THAT NOBODY REMEMBERS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WE HAVE A REWARD TO DEAL WITH,
AND HERE'S A LITTLE DILEMMA.
28 DAYS OUT HERE HAS BEEN VERY,
VERY TOUGH.
YOU JUST HAD A FIRE.
YOU LOST HALF YOUR TARP
AND MOST OF YOUR FOOD.
YOU'RE LIVING
ON A SPOON FULL OF RICE.
IF THERE'S ONE PERSON
FROM THIS WINNING TEAM,
NAONKA, BENRY, HOLLY OR CHASE,
THAT IS WILLING TO GIVE UP THE
REWARD,
FORGO THE BREAK FROM CAMP,
YOU CAN TAKE BACK
FOR THE ENTIRE CAMP
TARP AND ENOUGH RICE
TO GET YOU
THROUGH THE LAST 11 DAYS.
ONE PERSON STAYS BEHIND,
EVERYBODY ELSE GOES.
THIS IS A HERO MOVE
OR A HEROINE MOVE.
>> I'LL DO IT.
>> Jeff: HOLLY, NOT HESITATING.
>> I NEED TO TAKE CARE
OF THESE GUYS.
WHEN I GO HOME,
I'LL EAT AS MANY HOT DOGS
AS I WANT.
I HAVE 11 DAYS OF MY LIFE.
>> YOU SHOULD TO IT, MAN.
>> TELL HER TO SIT DOWN
AND YOU DO IT.
>> AND FOR THESE GUYS.
YOU GUYS GO HAVE FUN.
>> YOU'RE GOING
TO GO EAT TONIGHT.
>> EAT MY SHARE OF HOT DOGS.
HAVE MY SHARE OF CANDY,
BUT WE HAVE 11 DAYS LEFT.
>> SHE NEEDS TO EAT.
>> TO HAVE RICE.
I'LL TAKE IT.
>> Jeff: COME GET THE REWARD.
(APPLAUSE)
>> WOW.
>> THANK YOU, HOLLY.
>> THAT'S AMAZING, HOLLY.
>> AFTER I STOOD UP AND I TOOK
THE RICE AND THE TARP,
I TURNED AND I LOOKED AT NAONKA,
AND I GAVE HER A LOOK LIKE,
"I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT YOU DIDN'T STEP UP
AFTER YOU ARE LEAVING."
IT TOLD ME RIGHT THEN AND THERE
I MISJUDGED
NAONKA'S PERSONALITY.
I MISJUDGED THE PERSON
THAT SHE REALLY WAS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
WE ARE GOING TO MEET
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT
AND WE ARE GOING TO FIGURE
THIS OUT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
SMILES OVER HERE
BECAUSE THE FOUR
OF YOU ARE ENJOYING A REWARD.
>> THANKS, MOM.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YELLOW TEAM,
HEAD ON BACK,
GET SOME RICE COOKING,
GET THAT TARP PUT UP, GET DRY.
BLUE TEAM, YOU'VE GOT
A FUN AFTERNOON IN STORE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD OUT.
HAVE A GOOD TIME AT THE CINEMA.
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
>> GET THAT TARP UP!
>> IT'S GOING TO BE RAINING HERE
IN ABOUT 15 MINUTES.
>> AS MUCH FIREWOOD
AS WE CAN REAL QUICK.
>> LET'S GET AS MUCH FIREWOOD
AS WE CAN.
>> WHO WANTS TO DO THE TARP?
>> HOLLY, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THAT.
>> YES.
>> I JUST WANT TO BE DRY
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
LAST NIGHT WAS MISERABLE.
>> IT WAS BAD.
>> GRAB THAT CORNER.
>> AFTER THE CHALLENGE TODAY,
HOLLY STEPPED UP AND SAID,
"YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL FORFEIT MY REWARD
FOR TARP AND RICE.
I CAN EAT HOT DOGS WHENEVER."
IT WAS A PRETTY COOL GESTURE,
YOU KNOW.
HOLLY IS A GENUINE PERSON.
SHE LIKES DOING NICE THINGS
FOR PEOPLE.
IT WAS GREAT FOR ME.
I WASN'T GOING
ON THE REWARD ANYWAY.
SO NOW WE'VE GOT EXTRA RICE
AND AN EXTRA TARP.
>> GET IT OVER THAT OTHER ONE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO GO
GET FIREWOOD.
>> OKAY.
>> I JUST DON'T THINK...
>> I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
SOME ADVICE.
>> OKAY. PLEASE DO.
>> OKAY, THIS IS WHAT I TELL
MY DAUGHTER.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU CAME HERE FOR A REASON.
>> YES.
>> THE REASON IS
TO PLAY SURVIVOR.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU NEED TO SUCK IT UP
AND YOU NEED TO PLAY THE GAME.
IF YOU QUIT,
YOU'RE ALWAYS GOING
TO BE REMEMBERED
AS THE GIRL WHO QUIT
SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA 21.
>> I KNOW.
>> WHAT IS YOUR
NUMBER ONE REASON FOR QUITTING?
>> I JUST FREEZE AND FREEZE.
AND IT'S, LIKE,
THE SUN IS OUT
AND SO I CAN GET THROUGH
AND WORK THROUGH IT,
BUT IT'S LIKE
WHEN THERE'S RAIN...
>> BUT NOW I GOT YOU A TARP.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
I JUST THINK IT'S STILL...
THE WHOLE FOOD ISSUE.
>> I JUST GOT YOU MORE RICE.
>> I KNOW YOU DID.
>> YOU WOULD RATHER WALK AWAY
FROM THIS GAME
BEING VOTED OUT THAN TO QUIT.
>> BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH LONGER I CAN...
I CAN, LIKE, PUT UP WITH THIS.
LIKE, EMOTIONALLY,
I'M, LIKE, A WRECK.
>> HONEY, WHY?
WE GOT A TARP.
WE GOT MORE FOOD.
YOU GOT TO...
YOU GOT TO BE TOUGH INSIDE.
THERE'S GOING TO BE A LOT WORSE
THINGS IN LIFE THAN THIS.
>> HOLLY BRINGING
IN THE TARP AND THE RICE
DEFINITELY GIVES ME HOPE,
BUT FROM THE MOM'S POINT OF VIEW
SHE SAID,"SUCK IT UP.
YOU ONLY HAVE A FEW MORE DAYS."
BUT IT'S LIKE I'VE BEEN
SUCKING IT UP FOR 28 DAYS.
I HAVE NOTHING LEFT TO SUCK.
>> MY DAUGHTERS WANTED
TO QUIT CROSSCOUNTRY.
I SAID, "ABSOLUTELY NOT.
YOU STARTED.
YOU'RE FINISHING."
THEY ENDED UP BEING
STATE CHAMPIONS THAT YEAR.
YOU NEED TO SERIOUSLY THINK
ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
>> I WILL.
I KNOW I NEED TO.
>> ON DAY 5,
WHEN I WANTED TO LEAVE,
JIMMY JOHNSON SAID TO ME,
"IF YOU STICK THIS OUT,
EVEN YOU MAKE IT 10 DAYS,
THINK OF HOW PROUD YOUR HUSBAND
AND YOUR CHILDREN ARE GOING
TO BE OF YOU."
AND THAT HIT ME LIKE A WALL.
AND I'M LIKE, "I'M STAYING."
AM I HUNGRY?
I'M STARVING!
BUT I'M LOOKING TOWARDS THE END.
AND BY ME NOT QUITTING,
I HOPE THAT I'M GOING
TO BE AN INSPIRATION
FOR MY CHILDREN
THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
>> OKAY, SO MAMA HOLLY
JUST SAID WHAT SHE THOUGHT.
>> I THANK YOU.
>> YEAH!
YEAH, BABY.
>> OH, MY!
>> NOW SHOWING
GULLIVER'S TRAVELS.
LITTLE MOVIE NIGHT, BABY.
>> WOW!
>> YES!
>> THIS IS AMAZING!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> LOAD IT UP.
>> I'M HAVING A HOT DOG.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
>> KETCHUP I HAVEN'T HAD KETCHUP
IN 20-WHATEVER DAYS.
>> WALK INTO
THIS LITTLE GRASS HUT
AND FRANKFURTERS WERE COOKING.
THERE WAS FRESH-POPPED POPCORN,
THERE WAS EVERY KIND
OF CHOCOLATE CANDY YOU WANTED.
EVERYTHING, AND SO IT WAS GREAT.
IT WAS SUPER.
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> GOD!
THIS IS FREAKING RIDICULOUS,
Y'ALL.
>> I WISH HOLLY WAS HERE, MAN.
>> SHE TOOK ONE FOR THE TEAM.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS
EXTREMELY SELFISH OF NAONKA
TO OPT OUT OF THE GAME
AND THEN CHOOSE TO STILL GO
ON THE REWARD.
I MEAN, GO HOME,
GET A LITTLE BIT OF RICE,
AND YOU KNOW YOU'RE GOING
TO EAT WELL BECAUSE YOU'RE DONE.
AND THAT'S WHAT NAONKA
SHOULD HAVE DONE.
>> THIS IS INSANE.
>> THIS IS HEAVEN.
>> I WASN'T ABOUT TO STEP DOWN
BECAUSE I DIDN'T GIVE 110%
IN THAT CHALLENGE TO SAY,
"OKAY, WELL, YOU KNOW,
I'M ABOUT TO GO HOME ANYWAY,
SO I GUESS I'LL GO AHEAD
AND GET YOU GUYS THE RICE
AND THE TARP."
UH-UH,
I WASN'T ABOUT TO DO THAT.
I'M NOT NO FOOL.
>> OH, MY GOD!
CHEERS, BRO!
>> CHEERS.
JALAPEÑO ON THAT.
>> I LOVE JALAPEÑOS.
>> SHOULD WE WATCH THIS FLICK?
>> WE'RE JUST HAVING
A COLD DRINK.
>> OH, SHE'S SEATS
ARE COMFY-COZY.
>> OH, MAN!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
WE SAT IN A COMFORTABLE SEAT
IN 28 DAYS.
>> I THINK THIS MOVIE
IS GOING TO BE AMAZING.
I LOVE JACK BLACK.
>> JACK BLACK IS FUNNY AS HELL.
>> HE'S HILARIOUS.
>> GULLIVER'S TRAVELS, BABY.
BLACK IS THE NEW BIG.
>> PLEASE DON'T BE...
F-FANS.
(SCREAMING)
>> JACK BLACK!
>> FIRE!
>> SO FAT.
>> WE HAD SOME FUN AND,
YOU KNOW,
WE WERE LAUGHING, BUT, YOU KNOW,
NAONKA DEFINITELY CONCERNS ME
A LITTLE BIT.
THE WHOLE TIME
I WAS JUST THINKING,
YOU KNOW, PLEASE LEAVE,
PLEASE LEAVE.
GET OUT OF THIS GAME AND MAKE IT
A LITTLE BIT EASIER FOR ME.
(LAUGHTER)
(APPLAUSE)
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THAT WAS REALLY CUTE.
>> THAT'S A GOOD FLICK.
>> WE'RE GOING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
AND IT FEELS GOOD, YOU KNOW,
TO HAVE THIS ENERGY.
AND I JUST FEED OFF THAT ENERGY
AND IT JUST MAKES ME
FEEL EXPLOSIVE.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHERE LIFE WILL TAKE YOU.
IT MADE ME REALIZE
THAT I HAVE TO PUT EVERYTHING
INTO PERSPECTIVE.
IF I STAYED,
DANG, I COULD WIN
A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> WE'LL BE EXCITED ABOUT THE
FIRE RIGHT HERE
TO KEEP THE BUGS OUT.
>> GUYS, THIS IS A COOL SETUP.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HOLLY, THAT'S, LIKE,
ONE OF THE SMARTEST DECISIONS
YOU YOU COULD HAVE MADE.
>> THANKS, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
JANE WOULD HAVE DONE
THE SAME THING.
>> I KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> I WANT TO WIN.
QUITTING HAS NOT CROSSED
MY MIND.
WE'RE GOING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT,
WHICH AUTOMATICALLY IS NOT FUN,
YOU KNOW.
AND PURPLE KELLY AND NAONKA
ARE GOING TO DECIDE
IF THEY WANT TO GO HOME.
SO WE'LL SEE.
IT'S GOING TO BE INTERESTING.
>> WHEN JEFF
SAID TODAY THAT, LIKE,
TAKING THE TARP AND THE RICE
COULD REALLY, LIKE,
MAKE A DIFFERENCE IN YOUR GAME.
I THINK THAT IT, LIKE,
DEFINITELY CAN.
>> THINK POSITIVE.
>> ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN TONIGHT.
NOTHING IS SET.
AND I THINK
THAT'S THE SCARIEST PART.
THE TARP AND THE RICE
CANNOT REALLY GET ME
THROUGH THE NEXT 11 DAYS.
I'D LIKE TO THINK THAT IT CAN,
BUT I JUST NEED
TO REALLY THINK ABOUT IT.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF RICE.
>> I THINK HAVING A
GOOD AMOUNT OF RICE TONIGHT
IS BETTER THAN HAVING
A BUNCH OF CANDY AND POPCORN.
>> YEAH.
>> PRETTY HOT.
>> REALLY HOT.
>> DEFINITELY THE HARDEST
TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR ME,
THE DECISION
IS NOT GONNA BE FINAL
UNTIL I'M EITHER
WALKING BACK OUT
WITH MY TORCH OR LEAVING.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING
IN THE PEOPLE
RETURNING FROM THE REWARD.
NOW WE'LL BRING IN OUR JURY.
ALINA, MARTY AND BRENDA,
VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT,
SO LET'S GET INTO THIS.
WE ARE HERE BECAUSE TODAY
AT THE REWARD CHALLENGE,
NAONKA AND PURPLE KELLY
BOTH SAID THEY WANTED TO QUIT.
BOTH OF YOU GUYS
AT DIFFERENT TIMES
HAVE SAID AND DONE THINGS
THAT YOU LATER RETGRETTED.
SO I SAID TAKE THE AFTERNOON,
THINK ABOUT IT,
MAKE SURE THIS IS A DECISION
YOU WANT TO MAKE.
HOLLY, THERE WAS A TIME
WHEN YOU WANTED TO QUIT
THIS GAME.
>> UH-HUH. DAY FIVE.
>> Jeff: WHAT HAPPENED
THAT MADE YOU STAY IN THE GAME?
>> WHAT MADE ME STAY
IN THIS GAME
IS I WENT AND TALKED
TO JIMMIE JOHNSON.
AND HE SAID,
"HAVE YOU EVER QUIT ANYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE?"
AND I SAID, "NEVER."
AND HE LOOKED AT ME AND HE SAID,
"THEN WHY DO YOU WANT
TO QUIT THIS?"
HE SAID,
"YOU'RE A STRONG PERSON.
YOU NEED TO GO FORWARD."
AND IF IT WASN'T FOR HIM
TELLING ME THOSE WORDS,
I WOULD HAVE PROBABLY BEEN GONE.
AND NOW I'VE MADE IT THIS FAR,
AND IF YOU'RE GOING
TO MAKE IT THIS FAR,
WHY NOT TRY TO GO
AS FAR AS YOU POSSIBLY CAN?
>> Jeff: JANE,
LISTENING TO YOU TALK,
LISTENING TO WHAT
OTHER PEOPLE SAY,
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE EVERY DAY'S
A WALK IN THE PARK.
>> NO, EVERY DAY IS NOT
A WALK IN THE PARK WITH ME.
I KNEW I HAD DRIVE.
I KNEW I HAD DETERMINATION,
AND I KNEW I HAD THAT SPUNK
THAT WOULD HELP ME GET OVER
ANY HURDLE THAT CAME.
AND I'M HANGING IN THERE.
I WISH THEY WOULD HANG IN HERE.
YOU KNOW,
YOU DO HAVE TO HAVE DRIVE.
DO YOU HAVE
TO HAVE DETERMINATION.
YOU DO HAVE TO HAVE HEART.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE
THAT WILLINGNESS
TO GO FORTH THAT EXTRA MILE
TO GET IT DONE.
>> Jeff: SO, NAONKA,
TAKE ME BACK TO THIS MORNING.
WHEN DID THIS START FOR YOU,
THIS THOUGHT OF QUITTING?
>> UM, WHEN IT'S RAINING
LIKE THIS
AND IT GETS REAL WINDY,
MY JOINTS GET TO HURTING.
SO THIS MORNING IT HIT ME, LIKE,
REALLY, REALLY, HARD
BECAUSE IT STARTED POURING
AND IT GOT REALLY, REALLY WINDY,
AND I'M FREEZING.
I'M LITERALLY FREEZING.
I'M PROUD TO SAY
THAT I LASTED 28 DAYS.
I'M THE ONLY AFRICAN-AMERICAN
STILL HERE,
AND I'M A STRONG WOMAN.
I COME FROM A BACKGROUND
OF STRONG BLACK WOMEN.
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY,
HOW ABOUT YOU?
WHEN DID IT FIRST COME
TO YOUR HEAD
THAT MAYBE YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH?
>> IT CAME TO MY HEAD
THIS MORNING
AND EARLY THIS MORNING.
>> Jeff: WHAT HAPPENED?
>> IT WAS LIKE
THERE WAS GOING TO BE
NO END TO THE WEATHER.
IT WAS, LIKE,
THIS COULD GO ON FOR DAYS.
AND I KNOW THAT WE CAN ALL
PHYSICALLY TAKE THIS,
BUT MY BODY, I JUST FEEL
LIKE I AM BREAKING DOWN,
AND, LIKE, I KEEP THINKING,
CAN I REALLY STICK IT OUT
WHEN I PUT UP WITH SOME
OF THE WORST DAYS I'VE EVER HAD?
>> Jeff: BENRY,
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON THIS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST DON'T LIKE, YOU KNOW,
WINNERS NEVER QUIT,
QUITTERS NEVER WIN SORT
OF THING.
I WAS RAISED BY THAT MOTTO.
AND IT'S JUST FRUSTRATING FOR ME
TO SIT HERE AND LISTEN,
YOU KNOW, TO THESE TWO GIRLS
THAT ARE OBVIOUSLY, YOU KNOW,
VERY CAPABLE OF STICKING
OUT THE LAST 11 DAYS.
>> Jeff: FABIO,
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE IN AGE
BETWEEN YOU AND PURPLE KELLY?
>> ONE YEAR.
>> Jeff: DO YOU THINK
THIS IS AN AGE THING?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK IT'S AGE.
I THINK IT'S MENTAL WILL POWER
AND THE WILL TO BE HERE
AND WHAT YOU KNOW YOU CAN
GO THROUGH.
WE'RE THE SAME AGE,
AND I'M GOING TO STAY
TILL THE END, MAN.
I DON'T CARE
IF IT'S SNOWING OUT HERE.
I KNOW WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF,
AND I'M GOING TO STAY.
>> Jeff: SO, NAONKA,
WE RUN THE CHALLENGE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOUR TEAM WINS.
SO NOW YOU HAVE
THIS GREAT REWARD.
>> THE REWARD WAS BEAUTIFUL.
IT WAS LIKE A CELEBRATION.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT NOTHING
BUT THE GREAT THINGS
THAT HAVE HAPPENED.
I HAD A BALL TODAY.
AND I LOOKED AT IT LIKE,
LET'S HAVE A GOOD TIME.
>> Jeff: REALISTICALLY,
YOU THINK YOU HAD
ANY SHOT TO WIN THIS GAME?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: BASED ON WHAT?
>> BASED ON MY DRIVE
ONCE UPON A TIME.
>> Jeff: THIS IS AMAZING.
PLEASE, GO ON.
REGALE ME WITH A STORY, WOMAN.
>> WELL,
MY DRIVE AND MY ATTITUDE,
MY SPUNK, MY CHARM.
I MEAN, IT'S 28 DAYS.
>> Jeff: AND I JUST WANT
TO BE CLEAR.
YOU THINK YOU HAD A SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME?
>> I DON'T THINK, I KNOW I DID.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
SO AFTER THIS GREAT REWARD,
YOU WATCH GULLIVER'S TRAVELS.
DID YOU LIKE
GULLIVER'S TRAVELS?
>> I LOVED IT; IT WAS FUN.
>> IT WAS AWESOME.
>> GOOD MOVIE.
>> Jeff: YEAH,
YOU DUG IT, BENRY?
>> YEAH, IT WAS INTERESTING.
VERY RELATIVE
TO WHAT WE'RE GOING THROUGH.
HE HAD TO FIND IT IN HIM
TO OVERCOME A LOT
OF DIFFERENT OBSTACLES
AND IT DEFINITELY SORT
OF HIT HOME,
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE
IN WATCHING IT,
IT WOULD HAVE HIT HOME
FOR HER, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO AFTER NAONKA, CHASE,
BENRY, AND HOLLY WON THE REWARD,
I SAID,
"IF JUST ONE OF YOU IS WILLING
TO GIVE UP THE REWARD
THEY JUST EARNED,
YOU COULD TAKE HOME WITH YOU
A TARP AND A BIG TIN OF RICE."
NAONKA, YOU'D ALREADY TOLD ME
YOU WANTED TO QUIT.
YOU WERE ALREADY READY
TO GO HOME,
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN VOLUNTEER
TO TAKE ONE FOR THE TEAM.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO.
I WAS GOING TO GO OUT
WITH A BANG.
>> Jeff: DO YOU SEE THAT
AT ALL AS SELFISH?
>> I DON'T CARE
WHAT ANYBODY THINKS.
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT ANYBODY'S OPINIONS.
I'M STILL THE SAME NAONKA
I WAS BEFORE,
AND I'M STILL GOING TO BE NAONKA
AFTER I LEAVE HERE.
>> Jeff: CHASE,
YOU'RE SHAKING YOUR HEAD.
>> THAT WAS THE ONE THING
THAT I DID DISAGREE WITH.
IF I WAS GOING HOME,
I WOULD HAVE GIVEN
THE REST OF EVERYONE
THE TARP AND RICE.
>> EVERYBODY HAS
THEIR OWN OPINIONS.
EVERYBODY IS GOING TO THINK
THAT I MADE A MISTAKE,
OR I'M PUTTING MY FOOT
IN MY MOUTH,
BUT I'M CONTENT.
>> Jeff: JANE, WHAT IS IT
THAT A YOUNG PERSON
CAN'T SEE RIGHT NOW,
THEY CAN'T GRASP,
BECAUSE THEY JUST DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH EXPERIENCE?
>> WELL, THE YOUNG KIDS
ARE GOING TO FIND OUT
LIFE IS NOT A PIECE OF CAKE
UNLESS THEY'VE GOT AN EASY RIDE
FROM THEIR PARENTS.
YOU DON'T HAVE A CLUE
WHAT'S AROUND THE CORNER.
LIFE IS FULL OF ROCKY ROADS.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
AND LIFE IS NOT AN EASY RIDE
FOR, LIKE,
90% OF THE PEOPLE OUT THERE.
AND WITH THE ECONOMY
THE WAY IT IS RIGHT NOW,
JOBS ARE SCARCE.
SO IF YOU DON'T HAVE SOME SORT
OF DRIVE AND DETERMINATION
TO SHOW AN EMPLOYER
THAT YOU'RE BETTER
THAN SOMEBODY ELSE,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET HIRED.
THERE'S PEOPLE OUT THERE
THAT'S A WHOLE LOT WORSE OFF
THAN US RIGHT NOW,
AND THEY'RE NOT
PLAYING SURVIVOR.
WE ARE.
>> Jeff: ON THAT,
LET'S GET DOWN TO THE DECISION.
RIGHT NOW, NAONKA,
YOU HAVE A ONE IN NINE SHOT
AT A MILLION DOLLARS.
YES OR NO,
ARE YOU GOING TO STAY
IN THIS GAME
AND FIGHT FOR A SHOT TO WIN IT,
OR ARE YOU GOING TO QUIT?
>> I'M GOING TO QUIT.
>> Jeff: NAONKA'S GOING TO QUIT.
PURPLE KELLY,
YOU NOW HAVE A ONE IN EIGHT SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
YOUR ODDS JUST IMPROVED
WITH NAONKA QUITTING.
YOU'RE GOING TO STAY AND FIGHT
OR ARE YOU GOING TO QUIT?
>> I'M GOING TO QUIT.
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY'S GOING
TO QUIT.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> Jeff: THAT MEANS
THE REST OF YOU
JUST MOVED UP TWO NOTCHES
AND DIDN'T HAVE
TO VOTE ANYBODY OUT.
NAONKA, WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO WITH YOUR TORCH?
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THEIRS?
IT GOT SMUFFED.
>> SMUFFED!
>> IS THAT THE WORD, SMUF?
>> Jeff: BUT, NAONKA,
THEY DIDN'T QUIT.
PURPLE KELLY,
WHAT DO YOU THINK SHOULD BE DONE
WITH YOUR TORCH?
YOU GUYS ARE QUITTERS?
>> I THINK IT SHOULD BE SNUFFED,
TOO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
SO I'LL SNUFF YOUR TORCHES,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO KEEP THEM
HERE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THEY'LL BE A REMINDER
TO YOU GUYS
WHEN YOU COME BACK IN HERE
AS PART OF THE JURY
OF THE DECISION YOU MADE
TO QUIT.
ALL RIGHT, NAONKA,
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
>> THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> I HATE THAT, MAN.
>> I WANT TO PLAY.
(KISSING NOISES)
>> Jeff: YOU WANT TO GO?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: GO.
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY,
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD OUT.
WELL,
THERE'S A VERY CLEAR THEME--
DESIRE.
THAT WILL POWER THAT COMES
FROM WITHIN.
THERE ARE 10 DAYS LEFT.
YOU GUYS NOW HAVE
A ONE IN SEVEN SHOT.
NO MORE EXCUSES.
IT IS TIME TO STEP UP
AND START PLAYING THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> THAT'S REALLY... UP, MAN.
I MEAN, THAT'S REALLY TWISTED.
>> I GAVE HER
SO MUCH MORE CREDIT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR:
THE SEVEN PLAYERS
STILL IN THE GAME WANT IT,
AND THEY WANT IT BAD.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A FIGHT
TO THE FINISH.
>> Jeff: THE KNIVES COME OUT,
AND NO ONE IS SAFE.
>> THE ONLY PERSON THAT COULD
BEAT YOU AT THE END IS JANE.
>> WE'RE VOTING JANE OFF.
>> AND HOLLY WILL ABSOLUTELY
BE GOING HOME.
>> I JUST DON'T TRUST SASH.
>> FABIO'S GOING HOME.
>> CRAZY WHAT A COUPLE
OF HOURS CAN DO AROUND CAMP.
>> I AM VERY SORRY FOR ALINA,
MARTY AND BRENDA.
IT'S HARD TO LOOK AT THEM
AND KNOW THAT THEY COULD HAVE
POSSIBLY BEEN IN THE TOP THREE.
I FEEL BAD.
>> I FEEL LIKE I OWE NOBODY
AN APOLOGY, NOT EVEN MYSELF.
AND I HAVE
NO REGRETS WHATSOEVER.
I MADE IT FAR.
SO TO SAY THAT I DID THAT
IS A HELL OF AN ACCOMPLISHMENT
FOR ME.