>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR", IN AN EPIC BATTLE
BETWEEN THE YOUNG AND THE OLD,
FORMER N.F.L.
COACH JIMMY JOHNSON EMERGED AS A
LEADER OF THE OLDER TRIBE.
>> EVERYBODY IN THIS WORLD NEEDS
MOTIVATION
AND I THINK I CAN HELP MOTIVATE
THIS TEAM.
>> Jeff: BUT MARTY RESENTED
COACH JIMMY'S STAR POWER.
>> I WANT NOTHING TO DO WITH
JIMMY JOHNSON IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: LATER THE BALANCE OF
POWER SHIFTED IN MARTY'S FAVOR
WHEN HE AND JILL FOUND A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> OH, JILL!
THE CHALLENGE NOW IS HOW DO WE
MAKE IT WORK?
>> Jeff: AT THE YOUNGER TRIBE,
SHANNON CALLED THE SHOTS.
>> I JUST WANT TO SECURE US TO
GO TO THE FINAL THING.
>> Jeff: HE ALSO ALIGNED HIMSELF
TO ALINA AND KELLY B.
WHO HAD A CLUE TO THE IMMUNITY
IDOL.
AT THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, THE
OLDER TRIBE HAD THE MEDALLION
OF POWER WHICH ROE SIDES ARE AN
ADVANTAGE.
IF YOU USE IT, THE MEDALLION
GOES TO THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
AND THEY WILL HAVE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO USE IT
AT THE NEXT CHALLENGE
>> I'M GOING TO USE IT.
>> Jeff: PLAYING THE MEDALLION
TURNED OUT TO BE A SMART MOVE
BECAUSE IT HELPED THE OLDER
TRIBE WIN.
TYRONE SCORES AND WINS!
BACK AT THE YOUNGER CAMP, BRENDA
WAS ON THE HOT SEAT.
>> IF MY ALLIANCE IS DOING WHAT
THEY SAY THEY'RE DOING,
BRENDA IS THE FIRST ONE TO GO.
>> Jeff: SO SHE CONSPIRED WITH
NAONKA
TO DISMANTLE SHANNON'S MAJORITY.
>> WHAT I'M TRYING TO GET PEOPLE
TO GET SHANNON OUT.
>> ME, TOO!
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SHANNON WENT ON A TIRADE
THAT ALIENATED ALMOST ALL OF HIS
REMAINING ALLIES.
>> I'LL SPEAK MY MIND, THAT'S
WHAT I'M DOING.
>> YOU'RE DIGGING YOUR OWN
GRAVE.
>> I'M GOING TO GET THIS OUT OF
THE WAY, ARE YOU GAY?
>> Jeff: SHANNON WAS VOTED OUT
LEAVING ALINA AND KELLY B.
IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
18 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> BLEW MY MIND.
>> THAT WAS CRAZY.
>> REGARDLESS OF WHO THINKS IT
OR NOT,
I THINK WE GOT RID OF THE RIGHT
PERSON FOR OUR TRIBE.
WE NEED TO GO BEAT THESE OLD
PEOPLE.
>> I THINK THE FEELINGS FOR EACH
OTHER ARE CLEAR,
I THINK WE JUST NEED TO WORK IT.
>> JEFF REALLY POINTED OUT WE'RE
NOT UNITED
AND IT WOULD BE COOL IF WE
FINALLY UNITED.
COMING BACK TO CAMP AFTER TRIBAL
COUNCIL WAS SO FAKE.
FAKER THAN FAUX FUR.
>> I THINK IT'S A GOOD THING A
LOT WAS AIRED OUT TONIGHT.
>> I AGREE.
>> EVERYBODY ACTING LIKE THEY
ALL COOL WITH EACH OTHER.
"OH, WE'RE ONE BIG UNIT, ONE BIG
HAPPY FAMILY."
NO, WE'RE NOT BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN
DIVIDED.
SO ALINA, KELLY B.
AND JUD WERE IN PURE SHOCK
BECAUSE THEIR RINGLEADER SHANNON
IS GONE.
THEY HAD A PLAN AND IT DIDN'T
WORK, IT BACKFIRED.
SO YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
OKAY.
JUST KNOW SOONER OR LATER IT'S
GOING TO COME BACK
AND BITE YOU ON THE BUTT.
(\THEME SONG PLAYING\)
♪ ♪
>> GOT TO BE FRUIT, GUYS.
WHERE THERE'S MONKEYS, THERE'S
GOT TO BE FRUIT.
>> WE HEARD THE HOWLER MONKEYS
FROM THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE LAGOON TODAY SO WE WENT
TO SEE
IF WE COULD FIND A FOOD SOURCE
THAT THEY WERE EATING.
>> OH, WOW!
(\MONKEYS HOWLING\)
(\JIMMY HOWLING\)
>> WAIT, JIMMY'S COMMUNICATING.
>> THEY'RE LOOKING AT YOU,
JIMMY.
(\JIMMY HOWLING\)
>> I'M A LITTLE STAR STRUCK WITH
JIMMY JOHNSON.
OH, MY LORD.
HE IS HYSTERICAL.
HE'S JUST AT HIS SOUL IS
INSPIRING.
(JIMMY HOWLING)
YOU DIDN'T REALIZE I COULD TALK
TO THE ANIMALS.
>> WHAT'D THEY SAY IN.
>> THEY SAY GET YOUR ASS OUT OF
HERE.
(LAUGHTER)
>> NOW IF I HAD BRADSHAW WITH
ME,
WE'D REALLY TALK TO THOSE
ANIMALS.
>> I'M A LITTLE PISSED OFF SINCE
DAY ONE, MAN.
WHY DO WE GET STUCK WITH A
CELEBRITY ON OUR TEAM.
EVERYONE GOT GLITTER IN THEIR
EYES.
IF JIMMY JOHNSON WALKED ACROSS
THIS LAGOON RIGHT NOW,
THEY'D PROBABLY BELIEVE IT.
>> FISH!
>> THERE YOU GO, YEAH!
>> NOT VERY BIG BUT SOMETHING,
RIGHT?
>> IT WILL ADD FLAVOR TO THE
RICE.
FLAVOR TO THE RICE.
>> YOU KNOW, HE'S A THREAT,
ESPECIALLY
A THREAT IN A POST-MERGE
SITUATION.
I THINK YOU TAKE JIMMY JOHNSON
INTO A MERGE,
THAT WOULD BE A DISASTER.
>> OH!
ALL RIGHT!
>> YEAH, BUT THE THING IS, THIS
IS SO FAR
IN THE FUTURE YOU NEED TO CALM
DOWN.
WHAT YOU CAN'T DO IS GET
EVERYONE STIRRED UP.
RIGHT NOW EVERYONE'S ABOUT A
STRONG TRIBE.
SO I THINK WE SHOW THE IDOL AND
SAY LISTEN,
WE WANT TO USE THIS TO KEEP
ESPADA STRONG,
WE WANT AN ESPADA WINNER.
WE'LL SAVE THIS TO THE MERGE.
MARTY'S GOT THE IMMUNITY IDOL
AND I THOUGHT
IT WOULD PAY OFF DIVIDENDS IN
THE LONG RUN TO GAIN THE TRUST
BY SHARING IT NOW RATHER THAN
LATER.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK YOU SHOULD REAL QUICK GO
AND GET IT
AND SHOW IT TO EVERYBODY, QUITE
FRANKLY.
AND GO FROM THERE.
>> I GOT SOME REALLY HOT COALS
RIGHT HERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF THESE WILL
LIGHT, MAN, IT'S SO ASHY.
>> THERE YOU GO.
YEAH, BABY!
(\COUGHING\)
>> YOU ALL RIGHT, BRO?
>> OH, MAN.
EVERY TIME I GET UP FROM THAT I
JUST FEEL LIKE SPACED OUT.
(\LAUGHS\)
>> IT'S LIKE YOU'RE WEED OUT.
>> TINGLY, DUDE.
>> MY WHOLE STRATEGY, BRO, IS TO
BE OUT
IN THE OPEN AND MAKE PEOPLE
LAUGH AND BE CRAZY.
FAR OUT, BRO!
I'LL TAKE WHAT I CAN GET HERE ON
"SURVIVOR" ISLAND, MAN.
BUT IT GOES DEEPER THAN JUST OH,
HA HA,
KEEP HIM AROUND BECAUSE HE'S
FUNNY.
IT'S LIKE...
HERMIT CRAB ON MY FOOT.
(\LAUGHS\)
IT'S LIKE I WANT TO BE KEPT
AROUND
FOR MORE THAN BECAUSE I'M FUNNY.
I WANT TO BE KEPT AROUND FOR MY
MENTALITY,
MY SPIRIT, WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
CALL IT.
MY FACE FEELS TINGLY MAN.
>> FABIO, HE'S SO STUPID.
I CAN'T STAND HIM.
I CAN'T.
AND I KNEW THE FIRST TIME I LAID
EYES ON HIM
THAT I WASN'T GOING TO LIKE HIM.
HIS HAIR GOT ON MY NERVES!
SUCH AN AIR HEAD.
YOU JUST KNOCK ON IT AND YOU'LL
HEAR HOLLOWNESS.
>> OFF WHOLE, LIKE, FACE MASK
RING.
>> DO I?
(\LAUGHS\)
>> SO, GUYS?
I HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF AN
ANNOUNCEMENT?
I FOUND THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
(\APPLAUSE\)
>> WHOA!
>> SO I THINK THIS THING WILL
REALLY COME INTO PLAY
WHEN WE HERE IN A MERGE
SITUATION.
SO WE'LL PLAY IT WHEN WE REALLY
THINK WE NEED IT.
>> THAT ANNOUNCEMENT AND MOVE
YOU MADE RIGHT THERE
STRENGTHENED THIS TRIBE BY ABOUT
FIVE TIMES.
MY HAT'S OFF TO YOU.
(\APPLAUSE\)
WAY TO GO.
WHEN MARTY ANNOUNCED HE FOUND
THE IDOL AND WANTED TO SHARE IT
WITH THE TRIBE SO THE TRIBE
COULD USE IT TOGETHER
AGAINST THE YOUNG KIDS I WAS
LIKE WHAT A GUY!
WAY TO GO MARTY.
I'M THINKING HE'S A NICE GUY.
I WOULD HAVE KEPT IT FOR MYSELF
BECAUSE IF YOU THINK ABOUT US
CARRYING THAT KIND OF POWER
INTER A MERGE SITUATION,
WE BECOME INVINCIBLE.
>> BECAUSE IN FIVE ON FIVE,
THAT GIVES YOU YOUR ADVANTAGE,
BOOM, THERE YOU GO.
MARTY'S STOCK WENT WAY UP AFTER
THAT ANNOUNCEMENT.
JIMMY T.
WAS LIKE "WHAT A GREAT GUY, HE
DID THE RIGHT THING."
I THINK HE CAME OUT LOOKING
LIKE A SUPERSTAR SO IT'S GOOD
FOR ME IN THE LONG RUN.
THAT'S PRETTY COOL.
>> WHEN MARTY TOLD EVERYONE HE
FOUND THE IDOL,
MAYBE HE WANTED SOME INTEGRITY
POINTS, TEAM POINTS
BECAUSE PEOPLE WOULD PERCEIVE IT
THAT, HEY, HE'S A TEAM PLAYER,
ON BOARD WITH WHAT WE'RE
PLANNING TO DO.
I THINK MARTY'S SHADY.
I THINK HE'S FOR SURE DOING HIS
OWN THING.
>> MARTY COULD HAVE EASILY KEPT
THAT IN HIS POCKET AND NOT TOLD
ANY OF US AND BEEN IN A HUGE
POSITION OF POWER INDIVIDUALLY.
HE JUST KEPT US STRONG AS A
TRIBE.
THANK YOU, MARTY.
I MEAN THAT.
>> IT WAS NOT GOING TO BE A
SECRET
FOR LONG THAT I HAD THE IDOL.
THE ONLY WAY TO PLAY IT WAS TO
MAKE IT APPEAR
AS SOMETHING FOR THE TRIBE TO
USE FOR THE BETTER GOOD
TO MOVE US ALL FORWARD, TO BE
STRONG.
BUT EVERYONE KNOW IT IS IDOL CAN
ONLY BELONG
TO ONE PERSON AND THAT ONE
PERSON IS ME.
>> I GO SEE JANE'S LAUNDRY
SERVICES
AND SHE'LL HAVE EVERYTHING DRY
IN 15 MINUTES.
NO CHARGE AND A SMILE.
>> I SLEPT MAYBE TWO HOURS.
HUNGRY.
NOT AS EASY AS I THOUGHT IT WAS
GOING TO BE.
I'M STARTING TO GET CONCERNED
THAT THIS TRIBE
MIGHT THINK I'M A WEAK LINK.
BUT I DON'T CONSIDER MYSELF A
WEAK LINK.
LISTEN, THIS IS THE THING I
SIGNED UP FOR
SO I'M JUST GOING TO GO WITH THE
FLOW.
I MEAN, I DO HAVE A BAD KNEE,
OKAY?
BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE ME WEAK.
I'M AS STRONG AS...
I'M NOT AS STRONG AS TYRONE,
OBVIOUSLY.
I'M NOT GOING TO SAY THAT.
THAT WOULD BE CRAZY.
BUT I'M AS STRONG AS ANY ONE OF
THE WOMEN,
EVEN THOUGH SOME OF THEM ARE
BUILT LIKE MOOSES.
>> CAN YOU MOVE THAT?
>> MOVING A LITTLE SLOW TODAY.
DANNY'S REALLY STRUGGLING.
I KNOW HE'S DOING A GOOD JOB
TRYING TO HIDE IT,
BUT HE'S JUST...
FOR WHATEVER REASON,
PHYSICALLY HE DOESN'T HAVE IT.
SO IN OUR NEXT CHALLENGE,
IF HE'S A ROCK STAR,
CLEARLY HE'S BEEN PLAYING US
ALL A SHOW.
BUT I DON'T THINK SO.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK
IS THE ONLY PERSON
WHO CAN SHAKE SOMETHING UP?
>> ALINA.
UNLESS, YOU KNOW, HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOLS COME INTO PLAY.
THE THING IS,
WITH ALINA AND KELLY B.,
WE HAVE AN OPTION RIGHT NOW.
SO IT'S NOT CLEAR-CUT WHICH ONE
WE WOULD VOTE FOR
UNTIL RIGHT BEFORE TRIBAL.
>> TRIBLA COUNCIL
DREW A LINE IN THE SAND
AND I ENDED UP ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF THE LINE.
THEY'RE GOING TO NEED
FABIO AND BEN IN THE CHALLENGES
SO KELLY B. AND I
ARE NOT IN THE BEST POSITION.
>> I TRUST US FIVE
AND THAT IS IT.
IF I HAD ANYTHING
TO SAY ABOUT IT
NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL WE'RE IN,
I'M DEFINITELY...
EITHER HER OR K.B.
BUT SHE STILL IS A BIGGER THREAT
JUST BECAUSE OF...
SHE WAS RIGHT ALONG WITH SHANNON
AND THE WHOLE DRAMA THING.
>> MY ALLIANCE RIGHT NOW IT IS
CHASE, BRENDA, SASH, MYSELF,
AND KELLY PURPLE.
THAT'S OUR STRONG FIVE AND WE'VE
GOT TO GET ALINA OUT OF HERE.
IF WE CAN GET ALINA OUT OF HERE,
WE'LL SEND A SHOCK WAVE
TO KELLY B.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET, BITCHES.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
OLDER TRIBE GETTING YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW YOUNGER TRIBE.
SHANNON VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JIMMIE JOHNSON,
I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
>> FOR A SHORT TIME.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS
BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, BOTH
TRIBES WILL RACE OUT
INTO A FIELD TO COLLECT TEN
TRIBE-COLORED BARRELS.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED
ALL TEN BARRELS,
YOU MUST ARRANGE THEM
ON INDIVIDUAL PLATFORMS.
THEN ONE PERSON AT A TIME
YOU WILL TOSS SANDBAGS
ATTEMPTING TO LAND THE SANDBAG
ON TOP OF THE BARREL.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET A SANDBAG
ON ALL TEN OF THEIR BARRELS
WINS IMMUNITY.
IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION,
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR REWARD.
(\CROWD GASPS\)
>> Jeff: IT'S A "SURVIVOR"
GARDEN.
YOU HAVE SAUCES AND SPICES,
FRUIT, YOU HAVE A SUSTAINABLE
HERB GARDEN.
WHATEVER YOU'RE ALREADY EATING,
THIS WILL CERTAINLY
IMPROVE THE TASTE.
NOW TO THE MEDALLION OF POWER.
YOUNGER TRIBE, YOU HAVE IT.
IF YOU USE
THE MEDALLION OF POWER,
YOUR ADVANTAGE WILL BE
THAT TWO OF YOUR TEN BARRELS
WILL BE OUT OF THE FIELD
ON THEIR PLATFORM
WITH A SANDBAG ON TOP.
GIVE YOU A MOMENT
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
>> I THINK WE CAN DO IT
WITHOUT IT.
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE, ARE YOU
GOING TO USE IT OR NOT?
>> NOPE.
>> Jeff: NOT GOING TO USE IT.
YOUNGER TRIBE NOT GONNA USE
THE MEDALLION OF POWER,
GIVING UP A HUGE ADVANTAGE
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> WE'RE JUST PRETTY CONFIDENT
THAT WE CAN TAKE THEM
WITHOUT USING IT.
>> Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE WILL
PLAY STRAIGHT UP.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
GET STARTED.
>> THE MOST AGILE GUY, START
WITH THIS FIRST BARREL
AND GO GET THE WATER BARREL.
>> I'LL GET THIS ONE BACK HERE.
I'M GETTING THIS ONE
BY THE TREE.
>> OKAY, I'LL GET THIS ONE,
THEN.
>> WHO'S GOOD ON TOSSING?
>> THREE OR FOUR, FIVE TOSSES
AND THEN YOU ROTATE TO THE NEXT
AND PUT THE NEXT TOSS.
>> START OFF WITH TY, FIRST.
>> IF SOMEONE GETS
ON A HOT STREAK...
>> I THINK EVERYONE
SHOULD TRY IT.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, ESPADA!
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO, FOR
IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> Jeff: GOT TO GET ALL TEN
BARRELS BACK BY ROLLING THEM.
EVERYBODY ON A BARREL.
YOUNGER TRIBE HAS TWO BACK.
YOUNGER TRIBE HAS THREE BACK.
HERE COME A BUNCH OF BARRELS
FOR THE OLDER TRIBE.
ONCE YOU GET ALL TEN
OVER THE LINE,
YOU CAN START STACKING THEM.
>> OVER THE LINE!
>> Jeff: GO YOUNGER TRIBE.
OLDER TRIBE WITH
ONE BARREL LEFT.
START STACKING THEM,
OLDER TRIBE!
YOUNGER TRIBE OFF
TO A VERY FAST START.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE,
YOU NEED TO PICK IT UP!
YOU'RE WALTZING THROUGH THIS!
IT IS A RACE!
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
DAN, YOU NEED TO DO SOMETHING!
GET ALL TEN BARRELS
ON THIER PLATFORMS!
EVERYBODY ON THE MAT.
ON THE MAT BEFORE
YOU START THROWING.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE STARTING
TO TOSS BAGS.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: BENRY LANDS THE FIRST
BAG FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
TYRONE LANDS THE FIRST BAG FOR
THE OLDER TRIBE.
>> YES, BENRY!
KEEP GOING!
>> Jeff: BENRY LANDS A SECOND
BAG FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
TYRONE LANDS A SECOND BAG FOR
THE OLDER TRIBE.
>> NICE SHOT T.D.!
>> Jeff: TYRONE ON A FAST START,
OLDER TRIBE LEADS 3-2.
>> COME ON!
>> CALM DOWN!
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: TYRONE
WITH A FOURTH BAG.
CHASE NOW HEADING OUT
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
>> COME ON TY!
NICE!
>> Jeff: TYRONE WITH A FIFTH BAG
FOR THE OLDER TRIBE!
YOUNGER TRIBE QUICKLY FALLING
BEHIND IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> LET BENRY GO BACK.
>> Jeff: BENRY BACK OUT
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
(\APPLAUSE\)
BENRY SCORES FOR
THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
IT'S 5-3.
>> NICE!
>> IT'S NOW 6-3,
OLDER TRIBE IN THE LEAD.
>> BEN, DON'T STRESS.
>> NICE!
>> YES!
>> Jeff: IT'S NOW 6-4,
OLDER TRIBE LEADING.
>> THERE IT IS!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE
CATCHING UP NOW.
IT'S 6-5.
>> I WANT A SHOT AT THESE.
>> TYRONE WITH ANOTHER SHOT,
JUST MISSES.
>> YOU GOT THIS BEN,
THERE YOU GO.
NICE!
>> Jeff: BENRY TIES IT UP.
WE ARE TIED 6-6.
TEN BARRELS TOTAL.
TYRONE MISSES.
BENRY PUTS THE YOUNGER TRIBE
AHEAD!
YOUNGER TRIBE LEADS 7-6.
MAKE IT 8-6.
TWO BARRELS LEFT
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
>> TYRONE, YOU NEED TO MOVE.
>> TAKE A BREAK, T.D.,
LET SOMEBODY GET A SHOT.
>> JIMMY T., BE QUIET.
>> BENRY IS ON A ROLL.
THESE TWO BARRELS RIGHT HERE,
HAVE THEY TAKEN THE ADVANTAGE,
THIS CHALLENGE WOULD BE OVER.
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
BENRY MAKES IT 9-6
YOUNGER TRIBE.
ONE BARREL LEFT.
>> YOU'RE WASTING ME BACK HERE.
YOU'RE WASTING ME.
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE
FALLING APART NOW.
>> LET J.T. AFTER THIS ONE.
>> Jeff: ONE BARREL LEFT
FOR THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
JUST MISSES.
>> HE HAD A GOOD FEEL.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE
WASTING ME HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: TYRONE SCORES,
IT'S 9-7.
>> TAKE A BREAK.
>> HERE YOU GO, TAKE A BREAK,
DUDE, GET READY TO GO BACK IN.
>> Jeff: JIMMIE JOHNSON PUTTING
IN JIMMY T. NOW.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> COME ON, JIMMY T.!
>> Jeff: JIMMY T.
LANDS FOR THE OLDER TRIBE.
IT'S 9-8.
(\SCREAMING\).
>> Jeff: ON AND OFF.
>> KEEP IT GOING.
>> COME ON, J.T .
>> ALMOST, JIMMY!
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
>> Jeff: YOUNGER SIDE WINS
IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> NICE!
>> YOU'RE A ROCK STAR!
(\APPLAUSE\)
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
(\APPLAUSE\)
YOU DECIDED NOT TO USE THE
MEDALLION OF POWER,
YOU DIDN'T NEED IT,
BENRY, YOU DOMINATED
THIS CHALLENGE
AND WON IT FOR
THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
NOW YOU HAVE
THE MEDALLION OF POWER
TO USE AT THE NEXT CHALLENGE
AND YOU ALSO KEEP THE OLDER
TRIBE FROM USING IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
COME GET YOUR REWARD
AND HEAD ON BACK TO CAMP.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I'LL GET THE SAUCES.
>> AFTER WE WON THE CHALLENGE, I
WENT RIGHT FOR THE FRUIT BASKET
AND I COULD SEE THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE.
I GRABBED UP ONE SIDE AND
I SAW IT RIGHT AT THE BOTTOM
AND THEN I SAW NAY
LOOKING DOWN, TOO,
AND I WAS LIKE, OH, SHOOT,
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> KELLY B. SHE WAS SCARED,
I COULD SEE
THE LITTLE WHEELS TURNING.
SHE'S PROBABLY LIKE, "DANG.
OF ALL PEOPLE, WHY DID IT HAVE
TO BE NAONKA TO SEE IT."
SO I HAD TO COME UP
WITH A GAME PLAN.
AS SOON AS WE GET BACK TO
OUR HOME, I'M GOING FOR IT.
DAMN THE FRUIT, I'M GOING
STRAIGHT FOR THE PAPER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THE RESULT,
ANOTHER LOSS
FOR THE OLDER TRIBE,
SOMEBODY ELSE FROM THIS TRIBE
WILL BE VOTED OUT AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP,
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> WHOA, WHOA!
>> WOW.
>> YUP.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHAT IS THAT ABOUT?
>> LEAVING THE CHALLENGE,
I WASN'T GOING TO LET KELLY B.
OUT OF MY SIGHT AT ALL.
SO I'M WATCHING HER,
SHE LOOKS AT ME
AND I'M LOOKING AT HER LIKE
YEAH, I SEE YOU.
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU THINK I'M ABOUT
TO TAKE MY EYES OFF OF IT.
>> SORRY ABOUT SMUSHING
YOUR BANANAS.
I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO.
THAT PAPER WAS BASICALLY
LIKE A MILLION DOLLARS.
THAT'S THE LIFELINE
IN THIS GAME.
GETTING A CLUE,
THAT'S THE LIFELINE.
>> THERE WAS A NOTE?
COME ON, FABIO!
>> THAT'S WHY SHE JUST...
>> KNOCKED HER DOWN
AND GOT CLUE.
GOT A NOTE.
>> AND YOU SMUSH
ALL THE BANANAS?
>> THAT SUCKS SO BAD.
>> NAONKA AND I WERE CARRYING
THE FRUIT BASKET IN
AND THE NEXT THING I KNOW,
SHE JUST PUMMELED ME.
JUST PUSHED ME OUT OF THE WAY.
SHE WENT AFTER THE CLUE
AND THEN KIND OF WANDERED OFF.
I WAS PISSED BECAUSE ALINA AND I
REALLY NEED
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT, MAN.
>> COMPLETELY UNCALLED FOR.
>> I'M JUST GETTING SICK OF IT.
>> I SAW THEM TALKING "THAT
BITCH NAONKA, SHE GOT THE CLUE."
AND I KNOW ALINE IS MAKING THEM
SEEM LIKE
"SHE JUST PUSHED ME OUT OF THE
WAY, I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT WAS GOING ON!"
GO AHEAD, BE A FOOL, BECAUSE IF
IT HAPPENS AGAIN I'LL PULL YOU
AGAIN.
AND I'LL PUSH YOU SO HARD THAT
DAMN LEG WILL FLY OFF.
"THIS A CLUE TO A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT'S UP TO YOU WHETHER YOU SHARE
THIS INFORMATION
WITH ANYONE ELSE.
DECIPHER THE CLUES TO FIND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL."
IT'S GOING TO TAKE ME FOREVER TO
FIGURE THIS OUT.
YOU COULD SAY I GOT 'HOOD.
I SURE DID.
I GOT 'HOOD.
I DIDN'T GET GHETTO.
GHETTO WOULD HAVE BEEN "GIRL,
YOU KNOW I HAD TO WHOOP THAT
AND GET THAT, GIRL, YOU
TRIPPING, GIRL, UH-UH, GIRL."
NO, I JUST WHOOP!
IT'S THE GAME, IT'S THE GAME.
SHE HAS ONE LEG.
DON'T THINK THAT I'M GONNA BE
NICE TO YOU
BECAUSE YOU HAVE ONE LEG.
I'M NOT GONNA WHERE NICE TO YOU.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING.
MY NAME IS NAONKA, NOT FOOL.
>> YOU WANT TO SEE IT?
>> SURE.
>> "DECIPHER THE CLUES TO FIND
IT."
EQUALS WEST TREE?
SUNSET TREE?
>> SO WE KNOW IT'S OVER THERE
WAY SOMEWHERE.
>> WELL IT'S EIGHT STEPS WEST OF
SOMETHING.
>> I'M GETTING THROWN BECAUSE
THERE'S FEET HERE
AND AN ARM HERE.
>> ELBOW.
NAY SHOWED IT TO ME AND I THINK
SHE'S...
I'M THE ONLY PERSON SHE SHOWED.
I JUST KEEP THINKING ABOUT IT
AND THINKING ABOUT IT.
ONCE WE SEE WE'LL START
DEDUCTING.
DAMN THAT TREE LOOKS OBVIOUS.
SHE DEFINITELY IN MY EYES THAT
HAS POWER RIGHT NOW,
I'M KEEPING AS TIGHT WITH HER AS
POSSIBLE.
THANK GOD IT'S NOT IN ALINA AND
K.B.'S HANDS.
>> ALINA, SHE SHOULD BE SHAKING
LIKE A LEAF ON ONE BRANCH
AND THAT'S THE ONLY LEAF THERE
HANGING ON FOR DEAR LIFE.
>> THE CHALLENGE TODAY WAS
PRETTY MUCH OF A DISASTER.
WE ENDED UP LOSING BOTH REWARD
AND IMMUNITY.
IS NOT ONLY DO WE HAVE TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THEY WALKED OFF WITH A WHOLE
MESS OF BANANAS AND SPICES
AND IT WAS PRETTY TOUGH TO TAKE.
>> I'M GOING TO SPEAK MY MIND
ONE LITTLE PIECE
TO THE WHOLE TRIBE WHILE WE'RE
ALL HERE.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE I GOT SOME
TALENT ARE BEING WASTED.
COACH, EVALUATE ME.
AS YOU LOOK AT ME A LITTLE
BETTER I GOT SKILLED.
AND IF YOU LEAVE THEM ON THE
BENCH,
IT'S GOING TO COST US.
THE GUYS THAT ARE THE LEADERS
ARE SQUELCHING ME
BECAUSE I'M AN OBVIOUS LEADER
AND THEY KNOW IT.
IF THESE PEOPLE KNEW WHAT THEY
WERE DOING,
I WOULD BE THE LEADER OF THIS
TRIBE
AND I WOULD LEAD THEM WELL.
RIGHT NOW, JIMMY JOHNSON, HE MAY
BE CATCHING UP WITH DANNY
IN THE USELESS DEPARTMENT.
JUST MY OPINION, I'M NOT ASKING
FOR TOO MUCH,
I JUST FEEL LIKE I'M BEING
WASTED.
I'VE ALWAYS HAD A HIGH OPINION
OF MYSELF AS YOU ALL KNOW
FROM PAST PERFORMANCES AND I
KNOW I'M KIND OF A SHOW BOAT.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I DON'T HAVE
VALUE IN THESE CHALLENGES.
AND WE SHOULD ALL...
>> I THINK IT'S OBVIOUSLY
DISAPPOINTING.
I THINK TYRONE YOU HAD AN
AWESOME TEAR BUT THEN,
YOU KNOW, THERE WAS A BUNCH OF
MISSES IN THE ROW.
>> AFTER I DID THE ONES I DID,
THEY PROGRESSIVELY GOT HARDER
BECAUSE THEY WERE FURTHER,
OBVIOUSLY,
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE AN ISSUE
STEPPING OUT.
>> YOU ARE NUMBER-ONE GUY SO WE
WANTED TO START WITH YOU.
AND SO YOU STARTED MISSING THEM
SO THAT'S
WHEN I PUT J.T.
IN THERE FOR A FEW SHOTS.
YOU MADE ONE.
>> I DID HELP.
>> TYRONE, IF I MAY, KEEPING IT
REAL HERE,
YOU DID HAVE A BIG LONG COLD
SPELL BEFORE HE TOOK YOU OUT
AND EVEN WHEN HE DID WAS CALLING
YOU,
CALLED YOU SEVERAL TIMES AND YOU
DIDN'T WANT TO COME OUT.
YOU HAVE TO BE A TEAM PLAYER,
TOO.
>> TRUST ME, IT'S NOT ABOUT ME.
I JUST WANT TO WIN.
SOME PEOPLE SEEM TO THINK I WAS
MAD BECAUSE I GOT PULLED OUT.
NO, I WAS COOL WITH THE
ROTATION, WHATEVER.
IT WAS JUST DO WE WANT TO WIN OR
DO WE WANT
EVERYBODY TO TOUCH THE BALL?
YOU KNOW?
EVERYBODY CAN'T TOUCH THE BALL
ALL THE TIME IF YOU WANT TO WIN.
IT'S NOT LITTLE LEAGUE WHERE
EVERY KID GETS
TO PLAY "X"
AMOUNT OF INNINGS.
IT'S NOT.
>> YOU HAD OVER 50 SHOTS.
AND YOU STARTED MISSING THEM.
WE PUT J.T. IN AND I THINK
THAT WAS A GOOD MOVE.
>> OKAY, VERY GOOD.
>> I JUST THOUGHT WE COULD HAVE
PLANNED IT OUT A LITTLE BETTER.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
TRUST ME. IT'S NOT
ABOUT TYRONE DAVIS.
ALL I WANT TO DO IS WIN.
>> WE ALL...
THAT'S ALL WE ALL WANT
TO DO, WIN.
>> OKAY.
>> IT WAS A HEATED DISCUSSION
AND KIND OF ENJOYABLE
JUST TO WATCH
A LITTLE BIT OF TENSION
FOR A CHANGE IN THIS TRIBE.
I HATE TO SAY IT BUT I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE'RE FINALLY GOING TO GET
THIS TRIBE TO PLAY THIS GAME.
THIS IS REAL AND IT STARTS NOW.
>> I THINK HE'S TRYING
IN HIS OWN LITTLE WAY.
HIS KNEES AND HIS BACK,
YOU KNOW, HE'S...
HE'S IN TOUGH SHAPE, YOU KNOW?
>> WELL, Y'ALL GOT
TO HAVE A STRONG TEAM.
>> I'M WORRIED
ABOUT JIMMY JOHNSON.
I THINK HE'S FULL OF IT.
I MEAN, JUST PLAYING LIKE,
HEY, I'M NOT GOING TO WIN.
I DON'T BUY THAT.
SO I NEED TO REMOVE HIM SO THAT
PEOPLE WILL LOSE THEIR DADDY.
THEY'LL EITHER SHAKE AND CRUMBLE
OR THEY'LL HAVE TO COME TO ME.
>> NO, I'M GOOD. WHATEVER.
IN MY MIND, DANNY, COACH AND
HOLLY ARE THE SAME PERSON.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT ORDER.
>> I DISAGREE.
I THINK HE'S MORE STRATEGIC THAN
EITHER ONE OF THOSE INDIVIDUALS.
HE NEEDS TO GO FIRST.
>> YOU COME TO ME
AND TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
THE WAY I SEE IT,
DANNY, COACH AND HOLLY
ARE ALL EQUALLY WEAK PLAYERS.
MARTY FOR SOME REASON
SEES JIMMY AS A THREAT.
SOMEHOW HE THINKS JIMMY'S GOING
TO WEASEL OR WORM
HIS WAY INTO THE MERGE.
I DON'T REALLY FOLLOW
HIS LOGIC OR REASONING.
AND TO BE HONEST,
I WOULD PREFER DAN
BECAUSE I THINK
HE'S PHYSICALLY THE WEAKEST.
BUT HE'S LIKE, NO,
NO, COACH IS DANGEROUS.
I WAS LIKE, "WHATEVER."
YOU'RE THE PUPPET MASTER.
>> ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
NO MORE TALK ABOUT IT, THEN.
>> MARTY AND I ARE VERY SOLID.
I THINK THE NEXT ONE TO GO
IS GOING TO BE JIMMY.
I MEAN, YOU'VE SEEN HIM.
I'M IN MUCH BETTER SHAPE.
I'M IN MUCH, MUCH, MUCH BETTER
PHYSICAL SHAPE THAN HE IS.
SO WHEN THE SMOKE CLEARS
TONIGHT,
WE'LL KNOW WHETHER I GO HOME
OR JIMMY GOES HOME.
>> ARE WE STICKING TO THE PLAN
OF THE SAME...
>> YEAH.
GOT ANY SUGGESTIONS?
>> WELL, DO YOU?
>> (\LAUGHS\)
>> FOR ME IT'S KIND OF OBVIOUS,
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE PROBABLY TALKING
THE SAME THING?
>> I FEEL BAD FOR THE GUY
BECAUSE I LIKE HIM
BUT COACH IT IS FOR ME.
HE WAS NEVER A BIG JIMMY T.
FAN ANYWAY.
>> COOL.
THERE'S SOME PEOPLE
THAT ARE DEFINITELY SMART.
ACTUALLY, NOT THAT MANY.
BUT I'VE GOT THE STRATEGY.
JIMMY J.'S GOT TO GO FIRST
AND IT WILL SHAKE THE TRIBE
TO ITS CORE.
I'VE GOT DANNY SQUARED AWAY
AND I'VE GOT JIMMY T.
I'VE GOT JILL,
SHE TOTALLY DEFERS TO ME.
PEOPLE LIKE JANE AND HOLLY,
I MEAN,
LOOK AT JIMMY JOHNSON
AS IF HE WERE THE POPE.
SO THAT...
JUST PEOPLE BEING STUPID.
>> DAMN I WANTED A PIECE
OF PINEAPPLE AND BANANA.
>> I KNOW MY HEAD'S ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK FOR TONIGHT.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> NOBODY BROUGHT UP MY NAME?
SO YOU'RE SAYING
IF MY NAME COMES UP
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ME?
>> I WILL TELL YOU.
>> SO WHO ARE YOU WRITING DOWN?
>> I HAVE A FEELING
IT MIGHT BE DANNY.
>> WHO?
>> DANNY.
I REALLY WOULD LIKE TO SEE
THE WEAKEST PLAYER GO HOME.
I DON'T KNOW IF DANNY'S HAVING
THAT GREAT OF A TIME.
HE'S GOT AN INJURED LEG, OKAY?
SPIRITS ARE GETTING A LITTLE LOW
WITH THE LACK OF FOOD.
COACH IS KIND OF
MY FISHING BUDDY,
SO I REALLY DON'T WANT HIM TO GO
AT THIS POINT.
I REALLY DON'T WANT DAN TO GO
EITHER,
BUT WE WILL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
I DO NOT LIKE GOING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
HATE IT.
(\LAUGHS\)
>> OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> BUT...
>> I HOPE NOT, COACH.
>> IT'S BEEN AN EXPERIENCE.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
I SAID ALL ALONG I JUST WANT ONE
OF Y'ALL TO WIN A MILLION BUCKS.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE LIKE
MY FAVORITE PERSON HERE.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU GO.
>> I'M IN TROUBLE EVERY SINGLE
WEEK WE GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I KNOW THAT.
I THINK I'M GOING
TO GO BACK UP THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> I WANT TO KEEP
PLAYING THE GAME.
IT'S THE TOUGHEST THING
I'VE EVER GONE THROUGH.
I'VE GONE THROUGH TWO A DAY
PRACTICES,
THREE A DAY PRACTICES, BOTH
AS A COACH AND AS A PLAYER,
AND NOTHING COMPARES TO THIS.
NOTHING COMPARES TO IT.
>> MARTY'S PARANOID.
I THINK THAT MARTY'S VERY MUCH
ABOUT MARTY.
I HAVEN'T MADE UP MY MIND YET,
BUT JIMMY JOHNSON'S LIFE
HAS BEEN ABOUT MOTIVATING
AND LEADING MEN.
I'M WORRIED
ABOUT DANNY'S PHYSICAL ABILITY
TO HELP THE TEAM.
DUDE GOT AILMENTS.
YOU RAISE SOME VALID POINTS
FOR SURE.
BUT IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE BECAUSE
I GOT SOME OTHER PEOPLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S SOME PEOPLE THAT ARE
KIND OF SHYING AWAY
FROM MAKING THE TOUGH CALLS.
TYRONE'S ANSWER WAS NOWHERE NEAR
WHAT I NEEDED IT TO BE.
IT SHOWS HE'S NOT THINKING
THIS GAME THROUGH AT ALL.
I THINK THAT'S A HUGE MISTAKE.
I'D LIKE JIMMY JOHNSON GONE,
AND THOSE THAT WANT TO PLAY
WITH ME AND WANT TO PLAY ALONG,
JUMP ON BOARD.
DO NOT MESS AROUND WITH ME.
I MEAN, I'M PLAYING THIS GAME
FOR REAL,
AND I'M PLAYING
A SMART GAME HERE.
I JUST HOPE IT ALL GOES THE WAY
I'M PLANNING,
'CAUSE THIS IS
WHAT NEEDS TO HAPPEN,
AND IT NEEDS TO HAPPEN NOW.
>> Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT
TODAY'S CHALLENGE, MARTY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WE HAD A LITTLE BIT OF LEAD
GOING INTO IT, LOST SOME GROUND
AND JUST COULDN'T PULL IT
THROUGH AT THE END.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T.,
WAS THERE ANY FRUSTRATION
ABOUT HOW THINGS WENT DOWN?
WE SHOULD HAVE DONE THIS?
WE COULD HAVE DONE THAT?
>> WELL, AS IS MY WAY,
I ALWAYS WANT
A LITTLE MORE PLAY TIME,
SO I TOLD THE COACH
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
THESE PEOPLE HAVE BEEN WITH ME
FOR A WEEK,
I THINK
THEY HAVE SEEN MY SKILL SET,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY
I'M NOT GETTING A LITTLE MORE
COURT TIME, IF YOU WILL.
>> Jeff: SO YOU LITERALLY WENT
TO JIMMY JOHNSON,
AND SAID "PUT ME IN COACH,
I'M READY TO PLAY?"
>> OH, DURING THE GAME,
I WAS, LIKE,
"YOU'RE WASTING ME HERE, COACH.
YOU'RE WASTING ME HERE."
AND I THINK HE KNEW IT,
AND THAT'S WHY HE DID PUT ME IN.
HE KNOWS I GOT GAME.
>> Jeff: SO, JILL, IT SOUNDS
LIKE YOU GUYS ARE RELYING
ON JIMMY JOHNSON FOR SOME
STRATEGY AT THESE CHALLENGES.
>> I MEAN, EVERYBODY HERE IS
A LEADER IN THEIR OWN FIELD,
WANTS TO PLAY,
WANTS TO GO GET HIM,
AND SOMETIMES
THAT DOESN'T ALL GEL.
SO, I GUESS HE'S THE MOST
ACCOMPLISHED LEADER
OF ALL OF US,
SO WE OFTEN LOOK TO HIM.
>> Jeff: SO, JIMMY, IS YOUR
BIGGEST CONTRIBUTION
HELPING FORM THE STRATEGY
OF THE CHALLENGE?
>> I DON'T THINK
I'M REALLY FORMING THE STRATEGY
OF THE CHALLENGE.
I THINK I'M LISTENING TO THEM
AND LETTING THEM
MAKE THE CONTRIBUTION.
THE OTHER CONTRIBUTION I MAKE
IS, I HELP WITH THE FISHING,
AND IN THE CHALLENGES, THEY KNOW
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT ALL.
>> Jeff:
HOLLY, GIVE ME AN EXAMPLE
OF JIMMY JOHNSON'S
LEADERSHIP SKILLS.
>> I THINK THERE'S BEEN
MANY TIMES HE STEPS FORWARD,
AND WHEN WE'RE AROUND
THE CAMPFIRE,
THERE'S TIMES WHERE HE'LL SAY,
"OKAY, WE NEED
TO HAVE A TEAM MEETING."
HE TRIES TO BOOST THE MORALE
AS MUCH AS HE POSSIBLY CAN.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T.,
YOU LIT UP AND STARTED SMILING.
>> I WAS JUST ANXIOUS TO HEAR
WHAT THE ANSWER WAS GOING TO BE.
>> Jeff: REALLY? JUST EXCITED
TO HEAR
WHAT HOLLY HAD TO SAY, HUH?
I GOT TO ASK.
HOW ARE YOU GETTING ALONG
WITH JIMMY JOHNSON?
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK ME
AND JIMMY HAVE HAD A CHANCE
TO REALLY SIT DOWN AND TALK.
I KNOW HE NEVER
REALLY APPROACHED ME,
AND I NEVER REALLY
APPROACHED HIM.
>> Jeff: HOW IS IT POSSIBLE,
EIGHT DAYS
OF LIVING TOGETHER OUT HERE,
THAT YOU HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE
TO SPEAK?
CELEBRITY ALONE
WOULD MAKE MOST PEOPLE SAY,
"I'D LIKE TO TALK
TO JIMMY JOHNSON."
>> OF COURSE
I'M A BIG FOOTBALL FAN
AND A PATRIOTS
SEASON TICKETHOLDER.
BUT, UM, I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE I'M A THREAT
TO HIS LEADERSHIP ROLE
BECAUSE I AM A LEADER
WHERE I COME FROM,
AND I AM ASSERTIVE,
OFTEN SPEAKING MY MIND,
AND MAYBE HE DIDN'T WANT
TO BE BOTHERED WITH THAT.
IT COULD BE THAT SIMPLE.
>> Jeff: TYRONE,
WHAT'S THAT LOOK FOR?
>> I... THAT'S...
KIND OF BAFFLING TO ME.
THINKS HE MAY BE A THREAT
TO HIS LEADERSHIP ROLE.
I JUST FOUND THAT INTERESTING.
>> Jeff: JIMMY JOHNSON,
ARE YOU THREATENED BY JIMMY T.?
>> NO, AND, ACTUALLY,
I FEEL LIKE
I'VE GOT A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH JIMMY T.
WE NEVER HAVE SAT DOWN
ONE ON ONE
AND HAD LONG CONVERSATIONS,
BUT I'VE ALWAYS FELT
IT'S BEEN A GREAT RELATIONSHIP.
>> Jeff: SO, JILL,
YOU'VE LOST THIS CHALLENGE.
HOW MUCH DOES THAT WEIGH
ON YOUR MIND
AS THE TRIBE IS GETTING SMALLER
AND SMALLER?
>> IT WEIGHS A LOT
'CAUSE WE'RE GOING UP
AGAINST REALLY YOUNG,
STRONG-LOOKING PLAYERS,
AND I THINK
THAT'S OUR MOTIVATION
FOR NEEDING THE STRONGEST TRIBE
POSSIBLE TO GO UP AGAINST THEM.
>> Jeff: DAN, WHAT ABOUT YOU
IS STRONG IN THIS GAME?
>> I THINK I'M AVERAGE.
I'M NOT THE TOP OF THE LADDER,
BUT I'M NOT THE BOTTOM
OF THE LADDER.
>> Jeff: JILL, IS THAT TRUE?
>> WELL, SOMETIMES, AROUND CAMP,
DAN SEEMS A LITTLE STIFF,
AND MAYBE HAVING PROBLEMS
LIKE GETTING UP.
SO, BEING AN OLDER COMPETITOR,
IT'S, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
ARE YOU GOING TO BE ABLE
TO BRING IT DURING A CHALLENGE?
>> Jeff: JANE, DO YOU NOTICE
DAN STRUGGLING TO GET UP,
BEING A LITTLE STIFF,
AS JILL MENTIONED?
>> HE'S GOT A BIG SCAR
ON ONE OF HIS KNEES,
SO HE'S OBVIOUSLY HAD SOME SORT
OF KNEE SURGERY.
SO THAT MIGHT BOTHER HIM
GETTING UP AND DOWN, MM-HMM.
>> Jeff: DAN, ARE YOU AWARE
THAT PEOPLE ARE WATCHING YOU?
THEY'RE CHECKING YOU OUT?
>> YES, BUT I'M THERE,
YOU KNOW?
I'LL COME UP
TO WHATEVER I HAVE TO DO,
AND IF I DON'T MEET
WHAT THEY WANT ME TO DO,
THEN I'LL BE VOTED OUT.
BUT, UH, I'M THERE.
>> Jeff: SO JIMMY T.,
YOU GET BACK FROM THE CHALLENGE
KNOWING YOU'VE GOT TO VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHAT WENT DOWN?
>> I THINK, OVERALL,
THE TRIBE IS PLANNING
ON KEEPING ITS STRONGEST PLAYERS
AND REMAINING STRONG.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE TELLING ME
ALL THE TIME,
AND I'M ON BOARD WITH THAT.
BECAUSE THAT'S CERTAINLY
NOT GOING TO HURT ME, SO...
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE NOT ONE
OF THE WEAKER PLAYERS?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> Jeff:
WHO ARE THE WEAK PLAYERS?
>> YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT
TO CALL PEOPLE OUT.
BUT, UM, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WE GOT THREE
OR FOUR WEAK PLAYERS HERE.
I'M JUST KEEPING IT REAL, MAN.
>> Jeff: HOLLY, YOU THINK
YOU'RE ONE OF THE WEAK PLAYERS?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK I AM.
>> Jeff: JANE,
ARE YOU ONE OF THE WEAK MEMBERS?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> Jeff: MARTY?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
>> Jeff: HOW ABOUT YOU, YVE?
>> I DON'T BELIEVE SO.
>> Jeff: JILL?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
>> Jeff: TYRONE?
>> NEGATIVE.
>> Jeff: OKAY,
THAT LEAVES TWO PEOPLE.
DAN, ARE YOU ONE OF
THE WEAKER PLAYERS IN THIS GAME?
>> I DON'T THINK I AM.
>> Jeff: YOU DON'T THINK
YOU ARE, EITHER.
SO JIMMY JOHNSON, ARE YOU ONE OF
THE WEAKER PLAYERS IN THIS GAME?
>> YEAH, I'M THE OLDEST PLAYER,
AND ONE OF THE WEAKEST, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO THE ONLY GUY HERE
WHO ADMITS TO THINKING
HE'S ONE OF THE WEAK PLAYERS
IS JIMMY JOHNSON.
SO, TYRONE, YOU GOT
TO MAKE A VOTE TONIGHT.
IS THAT A FREE PASS,
VOTE HIM OUT?
>> UH, THERE'S DEFINITELY
OTHER DYNAMICS,
BUT YOU ASKED JIMMY JOHNSON
A DIRECT QUESTION,
AND HE GAVE HIS ANSWER BASED
ON A SELF-ASSESSMENT, YOU KNOW.
>> Jeff: MARTY,
HOW ABOUT FOR YOU?
WHAT'S THE GOAL
OF TONIGHT'S VOTE?
>> I THINK IN PART, I'M ANXIOUS
TO GET THE GAME
A LITTLE MORE ACCELERATED
AND A LITTLE MORE ENGAGED.
PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO START THINKING
ABOUT ALL THE FACETS
OF THIS GAME,
NOT JUST
WEAKEST-STRONGEST CHALLENGES.
THERE'S A LOT GOING ON HERE.
>> Jeff: MAN, IF I DIDN'T THINK
PEOPLE WERE THINKING ABOUT THAT,
THE LAST THING
I WOULD DO IS REMIND THEM.
>> WELL, I JUST THINK,
IT FEELS AS IF WE'RE DOING A LOT
OF SORT OF WAITING AROUND,
YOU KNOW?
AND NOW, I FEEL
THAT THE PACE IS PICKING UP.
AND CERTAINLY, GOING TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL IS A BIG DRIVER OF THAT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JANE, YOU'RE UP.
>> COACH, YOU SAID
YOU'D LISTEN TO EVERYBODY,
BUT YOU NEVER REALLY
LISTENED TO ME.
I TRIED TO GIVE MY INPUT,
AND IT FELL ON DEAF EARS, SO,
GO LONG.
>> Jeff:
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
>> Jeff: ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JIMMY JOHNSON.
DANIEL. ONE VOTE JIMMY,
ONE VOTE DANIEL.
JIMMY. THAT'S TWO VOTES JIMMY,
JIMMY. THAT'S THREE VOTES JIMMY,
ONE VOTE DANIEL.
JIMMY JOHNSON.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JIMMY,
ONE VOTE DANIEL.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT
OF SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA--
JIMMY JOHNSON.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JIMMY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> ONE OF YOU,
WIN A MILLION BUCKS, OKAY?
>> Jeff: WELL,
IN VOTING OUT JIMMY JOHNSON,
YOU VOTE OUT A PROVEN LEADER.
THE QUESTION IS, WHO'S GOING
TO STEP UP AND FILL THOSE SHOES?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:
NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR...
BATTEN DOWN THE HATCHES.
A FIERCE STORM IS ABOUT
TO WREAK HAVOC.
>> PUT THE BOXING GLOVES ON.
NOW I'M GOING
TO LET YOU HAVE IT.
>> Jeff: GET READY
FOR HURRICANE NAONKA.
>> YOU KNOCKED ME OVER?
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN...
>> I'M JUST LETTING YOU KNOW.
SCREW YOUR LEG.
KEEP IT AWAY FROM THE FIRE.
>> I HAD FUN.
BUT I WAS MISERABLE
THE WHOLE TIME.
AND I STILL LOVE THE GAME,
AND IT'S BEEN A GREAT ADVENTURE.
THIS IS THE MOST STRESSFUL TIME
I'VE EVER GONE THROUGH
IN MY LIFE,
AND I'M INCLUDING SUPER BOWLS
AND COLLEGIATE
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIPS.
I INITIALLY SAID,
"KEEP YOUR STRONGEST MEMBERS."
I OBVIOUSLY WASN'T ONE
OF THE STRONGEST MEMBERS.
I THINK THEY WILL COME TOGETHER
AND BE SUCCESSFUL.