>> Jeff: THIS IS NICARAGUA:
REMOTE, MYSTERIOUS, DANGEROUS.
STRADDLED BETWEEN
THE RAGING WATERS
OF THE PACIFIC OCEAN
AND THE CARIBBEAN SEA.
IT'S WHERE ANCIENT RAIN FORESTS
BATTLE FOR SURVIVAL
AGAINST SOME OF THE WORLD'S
YOUNGEST
AND MOST ACTIVE VOLCANOS.
THIS RUGGED LAND
HAS RESISTED TAMING
SINCE THE DAYS
OF THE CONQUISTADORS.
AND IT IS WHERE 20 AMERICANS
HAVE ALREADY BEGUN
THE ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME.
>> EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK THERE'S
MONKEYS HANGING FROM THINGS.
THERE'S DANGEROUS ANIMALS HERE.
IT'S LIKE...
IT'S REAL.
THERE'S NO FENCES LIKE THE ZOO.
>> I'M JIMMY JOHNSON.
I'M 66 YEARS OLD AND I'VE WON
TWO COLLEGIATE
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIPS.
I'VE WON TWO SUPERBOWLS.
WHAT COULD TOP IT OFF BETTER
THAN TO WIN "SURVIVOR"?
>> Jeff: THEY THINK THEY'VE
ALREADY
BEEN DIVIDED INTO TWO TRIBES.
THOUGH THEY HAVE NOT SPOKEN,
FIRST IMPRESSIONS
ARE ALREADY FORMING.
>> I NOTICE THE OLDER GENTLEMAN
LOOKS LIKE A MAFIA BOSS
AND HE LOOKS LIKE HE WANTS TO
BOSS PEOPLE AROUND
AND I'M NOT THE KIND
OF CHARACTER
THAT LIKES HIS BUTTONS PUSHED.
>> THERE'S AN OLD
GRAY-HAIRED GUY
THAT'S PISSING ME OFF ALREADY.
HE SEEMS LIKE THE KIND OF GUY
WHO'S GOING TO STEP
INTO THE LEADERSHIP POSITION.
I HOPE HE DOES BECAUSE HE'LL
JUST GET KICKED OFF RIGHT AWAY.
>> JEFF: FORCED
TO WORK TOGETHER,
THEY MUST LEARN TO ADAPT
OR THEY'LL BE VOTED OUT.
>> I'M SINGLE.
(\LAUGHS\)
I AM SINGLE, SINGLE, SINGLE.
VERY SINGLE.
AND FLIRTING IS SOMETHING
I'M GOING TO USE IF I HAVE TO.
>> JEFF: IN THE END, ONLY ONE
WILL REMAIN TO CLAIM
THE MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE,
ONE SURVIVOR!
(\THEME SONG PLAYING\)
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR:
NICARAGUA."
WOMAN IN THE PLAID,
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> EVE.
>> JEFF: YOU'VE HAD
A LITTLE BIT OF TIME
TO SPEND WITH THESE PEOPLE.
CAN YOU TELL THINGS ABOUT PEOPLE
FROM THE WAY THEY WALK?
FROM THE WAY THEY'RE LOOKING AT
EACH OTHER?
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
YOU CAN TELL A LOT
ABOUT A PERSON
NOT JUST THE WAY THEY'RE WALKING
BUT BY THE WAY THEY'RE WATCHING
OTHER PEOPLE.
>> I WAS BORN WITH
A BIRTH DEFECT THAT FORCED
THE AMPUTATION OF MY RIGHT LEG
WHEN I WAS SIX MONTHS OLD.
I THINK INITIALLY I'M KEEPING
EVERYTHING A SECRET.
I DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO MAKE
ASSUMPTIONS
ABOUT MY PHYSICAL ABILITY
AND THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE DO.
>> Jeff: GUY IN THE BLUE,
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> MARTY.
>> Jeff: THINK YOU'VE PICKED UP
ANYTHING BASED ON EYE CONTACT?
>> YOU CAN TELL PEOPLE ARE
"THIS IS MY TEAM, THIS IS WHO
I'M GOING TO BE WITH."
SO PEOPLE ARE CHECKING
EACH OTHER OUT.
AS I'M LOOKING AROUND THE GROUP
RIGHT NOW,
I SEE JIMMY JOHNSON,
AN N.F.L. COACH.
I WANT NOTHING TO DO WITH
JIMMY JOHNSON IN THIS GAME.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY THE HELL
HE'S EVEN HERE.
AND I'D RATHER HAVE HIM
ON THE OTHER TRIBE, FRANKLY.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY
TO GET STARTED?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
HIDDEN SOMEWHERE DOWN THAT
LAGOON
IS A MEDALLION OF POWER.
THE MEDALLION OF POWER
COULD GIVE YOU HUGE ADVANTAGE
IN THIS GAME.
THE PERSON WHO RETURNS WEARING
THE MEDALLION OF POWER
CLAIMS IT FOR THEIR TRIBE.
THIS IS NOT
AN INDIVIDUAL REWARD.
MAKE SENSE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: YOU CAN GO
ANY TIME YOU WANT.
>> SOMEBODY'S GOT TO THE RUN
TO THE RIGHT;
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO RUN
TO THE LEFT.
>> Jeff: PEOPLE ARE
SCATTERED EVERYWHERE
LOOKING FOR THE MEDALLION
OF POWER.
>> KEEP LOOKING!
KEEP LOOKING.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> VERY GOOD!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY HEAD ON BACK.
>> ONE OF OURS.
>> YES, SIR.
>> WHAT A WAY TO START.
I DON'T KNOW YOUR NAME
BUT YOU DID A GREAT JOB!
>> Jeff: GUYS, COME ON BACK IN.
>> I NOTICED THERE WAS A GIRL
WITH A LIMP.
SHE HAS DARKER BROWN HAIR
AND I COULDN'T TELL
WHAT WAS UP WITH IT.
LIKE, I THINK THAT SHE, LIKE,
MAYBE HAS, LIKE, A HIP PROBLEM?
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH THAT.
>> Jeff: MARTY, WHAT'S YOUR TAKE
ON BRENDA HAVING
THE MEDALLION OF POWER?
>> I THINK IT'S A KILLER.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO WIN ANYTHING
THROWN AT US AND TO BE THE TRIBE
TO WIN THE FIRST THING, I THINK
BODES REALLY WELL FOR US.
>> Jeff: IT WOULD BE GREAT
IF IT WERE THAT WAY.
UNFORTUNATELY, MARTY,
THIS IS NOT THE WAY
THE TRIBES ARE GOING
TO BE DIVIDED.
WE'RE NOW GOING
TO DIVIDE INTO TRIBES.
IF YOU ARE 40 AND OLDER
YOU'RE OVER HERE.
(\LAUGHTER\)
>> HEY!
HEY!
>> Jeff: IF YOU ARE 30
AND YOUNGER, YOU'RE OVER HERE.
>> DAMN, MAN, I WANTED THE OLD
FOOTBALL COACH, MAN!
>> OH, GOD!
>> JIMMY JOHNSON!
>> Jeff: DIVIDE IT UP!
LET'S GO.
>> YOUNG GUNS!
>> I'M YOUNG AT HEART!
OH, MAN!
THE OLDER ONES HERE,
THE YOUNGER ONES THERE.
I WAS LOOKING FORWARD TO SOME OF
THOSE YOUNG PEOPLE CARRYING ME.
(\LAUGHS\)
I DON'T WANT ANY
OF THE OLD PEOPLE WITH ME.
>> WHEN THE SWITCH CAME,
MY FIRST THOUGHT WAS OH, DAMN.
THE ANTIQUES HAVE THE BEST COACH
YOU COULD ASK FOR.
THEY'VE GOT A SUPER BOWL WINNING
COACH ON THEIR TEAM.
HE'S A GREAT LEADER.
THAT'S WHAT HE'S DONE
HIS WHOLE LIFE.
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE,
YOU ARE ESPADA.
YOU'RE WEARING BLUE.
YOUNGER TRIBE, YOU'RE CALLED
LA FLOR, YOU'RE WEARING YELLOW.
PUT YOUR BUFFS ON.
MAKE IT OFFICIAL.
>> WHERE DO YOU PUT IT?
>> I THINK IT CAN GO
ON YOUR HEAD.
>> I'LL HAVE TO MESS UP MY HAIR.
IT'S GOING TO BE MESSED UP
FOR A WHILE ANYWAY.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, YOU WON
THE MEDALLION OF POWER
FOR YOUR TRIBE.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH POWER
IT HAS,
ALL YOU KNOW IS THAT IT
IS FOR YOUR TRIBE.
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO MAKE A DECISION.
YOU CAN HOLD ON
TO THIS UNKNOWN POWER
AND GET A CHANCE TO USE IT
LATER IN THE GAME
OR YOU CAN TRADE IT RIGHT NOW
FOR FIRE
IN THE FORM OF FLINT
AND A CRATE
FULL OF FISHING GEAR.
YOU'VE GOT MASK, FINS, LINE,
HOOKS AND A SPEAR
TO GO ALONG WITH IT.
SO AS A TRIBE
HERE'S WHAT YOU'RE DECIDING.
DO YOU KEEP POWER IN THE GAME
OR DO YOU GIVE IT UP
FOR A QUICK START BACK AT CAMP?
WHAT YOU DON'T KEEP
THE OTHER TRIBE GETS.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> I SAY WE KEEP IT BECAUSE THE
LONGER WE STAY IN
THE MORE OPPORTUNITIES
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE.
>> KEEP IT.
>> THE MEDALLION THREW
EVERYTHING FOR A LOOP.
I WANT TO KEEP IT.
I LIKE THE FACT THAT IT'S POWER.
POWER.
>> I HOPE THEY KEEP IT.
>> I DO, TOO.
>> FIRE AND FISH.
FIRE'S GOING TO BE
SO IMPORTANT EARLY.
>> DECIDE, CHILDREN.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S...
DUDE, WE'VE GOT TO FISH.
DO WE WANT FIRE OR FISH, DUDE?
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THE DECISION?
ARE YOU GOING TO KEEP POWER OR
TRADE IT FOR THE FISHING GEAR?
>> Jeff: SO HERE'S WHAT YOU'RE
DECIDING: DO YOU KEEP POWER
IN THE GAME OR ARE YOU GOING TO
TRADE IT FOR THE FISHING GEAR?
>> WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
THE FISHING GEAR.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BRENDA,
TAKE IT OFF
AND GIVE IT TO SOMEBODY
ON THE OTHER TRIBE.
OLDER TRIBE, YOU'LL GET A CHANCE
TO PLAY THAT MEDALLION OF POWER
AT SOME POINT LATER IN THE GAME.
>> WE GOT POWER,
WHATEVER IT MEANS.
(\LAUGHTER\)
>> WE'LL FIND OUT.
>> AND IT'S GOLD.
DON'T WINNERS CARRY GOLD?
>> Jeff: ESPADA, HEAD OUT THAT
WAY, LA FLOR, HEAD OUT THAT WAY.
>> I FIGURE THE OLD PEOPLE
NEED THE MEDALLION OF POWER
MORE THAN WE DO.
I DON'T WANT TO UNDERESTIMATE
THE OLD PEOPLE BUT I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL BE ABLE TO HANDLE
SOME CHALLENGES.
THERE'S NO REASON WHY WE SHOULD
LOSE TO THEM.
>> MARTY?
JIMMY.
>> JIMMY...
JIMMY?
>> JIMMY J.!
JUST CALL ME JIMMY.
OH, MAN!
ALL THE ADVENTURES I'VE HAD
IN THE PAST, I WAS IN CHARGE.
I CAN FIRE PLAYERS,
I COULD RECRUIT PLAYERS,
I COULD SIGN THEM.
OUT HERE I DON'T HAVE
THE CONTROL.
SO WE'VE GOT TO GET THE FLOOR
OF THE SHELTER.
MAYBE SOMEBODY'S GOING TO BE
INFATUATED WITH ME
BEING HEAD COACH JIMMY JOHNSON
SUPERBOWL WINNER.
WELL, I'LL PLAY ON THAT.
I'LL PLAY SUPERSTAR STATUS.
SOME OF THESE OTHER PLAYERS
MAY RESENT THAT.
MAYBE THEY'RE
PHILADELPHIA EAGLE FANS
OR WASHINGTON RED SKIN FANS.
>> THAT'S JIMMY JOHNSON.
>> THAT CAN'T BE.
JIMMY JOHNSON WAS THE COACH
OF THE MIAMI DOLPHINS
AND DALLAS COWBOYS.
>> THAT'S HIM.
>> SO I'VE GOT TO WORK ON EACH
PARTICULAR CONTESTANT
TO WIN THEM OVER
BECAUSE IF I DON'T
I'LL BE A TARGET AND THEY'LL
VOTE ME OUT EARLY.
>> I REALLY LIKE YOU.
THE FIRST TIME I SAW YOU
I GOT A GOOD FEELING ABOUT THAT
AND I TRUST YOU.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AGREE.
>> OKAY.
I'M WITH YOU ALL THE WAY.
>> BACK IN SOUTH DAKOTA COACHING
THE SWIM TEAM YOU HAVE TO DEAL
WITH A LOT OF DIFFERENT
PERSONALITIES
AND YOU STILL HAVE TO HOLD YOUR
COMPOSURE AT THE SAME TIME.
SO I'M A VERY GOOD JUDGE
OF PEOPLE.
THE FIRST TIME I SAW WENDY
I TRUSTED HER,
AND MOST OF THE TIME
I DO READ PEOPLE VERY WELL.
YOU GOT MY WORD.
>> HOLLY SAID SHE WANTED TO BE
IN AN ALLIANCE WITH ME
AND I THOUGHT THAT WAS AWESOME,
BUT I WASN'T EXPECTING IT
SO SOON.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M NAIVE.
MY BROTHER CALLS ME SHELTERED
AND THAT'S KIND OF LIKE NAIVE.
I GOT THREE!
THIS IS MY THIRD!
BEING A GOAT RANCHER,
YOU'RE WITH A LOT OF GOATS,
YOU DON'T MEET A LOT OF PEOPLE.
MY STRATEGY FROM THE BEGINNING
OF THE GAME
IS TAKE BABY STEPS FIRST, NOT BE
THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OFF.
MY HUSBAND THINKS I'M GOING TO
BE THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OFF
BECAUSE HE THINKS I TALK A LOT.
SO I THINK I'M GOING TO BITE
MY TONGUE
AND HIDE MY TRUE SELF
FROM THE TRIBE MATES.
>> WENDY JO, WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
>> FROM MONTANA.
>> AND YOU LIKE HORSES?
>> I DO!
>> SHE'S A LITTLE WEIRD.
>> WE GOT FIRE NOW.
>> HUH?
>> WE'LL HAVE FIRE NOW.
>> OKAY.
OH, YEAH, YOU GOT THAT.
>> I CAN DO IT.
WHO'S GOT THE GLASSES?
THEY THINK I'M SOME MIDDLE AGED
HOUSEWIFE THAT TOOTLES AROUND
THE HOUSE ALL DAY LONG,
THEY ARE IN FOR A BIG SURPRISE.
BECAUSE THAT'S DEFINITELY
NOT ME.
I NEED TO GET IT
REALLY CONCENTRATED
RIGHT ON THAT SMALL SPOT.
I'M 56 YEARS OLD
AND I'M THE TYPE OF PERSON
THAT STAYS BUSY
ALL THE TIME DOING THINGS.
I JUST DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING I CAN'T DO.
WHERE THERE'S SMOKE
THERE WILL BE FIRE.
WINNING THE MILLION DOLLARS
IS REAL IMPORTANT TO ME
BECAUSE IT WILL HELP ME
PAY OFF MY FARM,
AND THE FACT THAT I LOST MY
HUSBAND IN '09, IT MEANS I WOULD
NOT HAVE TO WORK
AS HARD AS I DO.
BUT HIS SPIRIT I KNOW
IS STILL WITH ME.
AND THAT'S WHAT KEEPS ME GOING.
>> THERE YOU GO!
THERE YOU GO!
HERE YOU GO!
FIRE!
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
KEEP IT GOING, GUYS.
>> JANE, YOU ROCK!
>> IS THAT FRICTION OR GLASSES?
>> GLASSES, BABY.
>> GLASSES, HONEY.
>> KILLER.
THEY GAVE UP THE MEDALLION
AND WHAT DID THEY GET?
JANE STARTED THE FIRE LITERALLY
WITHIN HALF AN HOUR.
THE FACT THAT WE MADE FIRE
THAT QUICKLY,
IT REASSURED US ALL
THAT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE THIS THING.
ESPADA RULES!
WE'VE GOT JUST AS MUCH GOING
FOR US AS THE YOUNG GROUP DOES.
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
>> HIGH FIVES ALL AROUND.
BENRY.
>> BENRY?
>> NICE TO MEET YOU GUYS.
THIS GAME THAT'S OLD GUYS
VERSUS YOUNG GUYS,
WE KNOW WE'RE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO DOMINATE.
GREAT BEACH, GREAT WAVES,
BEAUTIFUL GIRLS.
DOESN'T GET MUCH BETTER
THAN THAT, RIGHT?
>> DO WE HAVE A MACHETE?
>> WE HAVE ONE RIGHT HERE.
>> WE CAN CATCH RAINWATER
AND ALL KINDS OF STUFF.
AS SOON AS WE SAW 30 AND UNDER
IT WAS LIKE THESE ARE MY PEOPLE!
THIS IS GOING TO BE
A LOT OF FUN.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'D BE GOOD
IN THE WATER.
OR NOT.
OOH!
OW!
(\LAUGHTER\)
>> DAMN, THAT WAS IN THERE!
>> THE GUY WITH THE LONG BLOND
HAIR, HE'S A DUMB BLOND.
I MEAN, I NEVER REALLY
CALLED A GUY
A DUMB BLOND BEFORE
BUT HE'S A DUMB BLOND.
>> OW!
OW!
DAMN!
>> BLOND-HEAD KID,
THE ONE THAT LOOKS LIKE FABIO.
DUDE, HE'S JUST RETARDED.
>> WE'VE GOT TO GET MORE BAMBOO.
>> YOU'RE FABIO, YOU GO GET IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE NAME FABIO, MAN,
I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE
I WAS BEING CALLED THAT
AT FIRST.
>> I'M GOING TO GO HELP FABIO.
>> DO THAT, HE NEEDS IT.
DUDE IS AN IDIOT, DAMN.
>> FABIO, LIKE, RIDES
A WHITE HORSE AND DOES
BUTTER COMMERCIALS
AND IS KIND OF A CHEESE BALL.
WHATEVER.
DUDE, I DON'T CARE
WHAT THEY CALL ME.
I'M GONNA WIN
THE MILLION DOLLARS
SO I GUESS MY NICK NAME
IS FABIO.
TIMBER!
>> OKAY, LOOK, I FEEL
THAT ME AND YOU
WILL BE THE STRONGEST
IN CHALLENGES.
WITHOUT ME AND YOU
I THINK THEY'RE SCREWED.
>> YOU AND I ARE DEFINITELY
GOING TO BE THE STRONGEST
AS FAR AS JUST STRENGTH WISE.
WE MAY NOT BE THE BEST SWIMMERS
OR SOMETHING.
>> I WON'T BE THE BEST SWIMMER
BUT STRENGTH WISE
ANY KIND OF ATHLETIC
ABILITY WISE...
>> THAT'S A TARGET ON OUR BACK.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT BECAUSE THEY SEE
ALPHA MALES BEING TARGETED.
THAT'S WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT ME AND
YOU STICKING DOWN TO NUMBER TWO.
ROB AND RUSSELL COULD HAVE RAN
IT LAST YEAR.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU
BUT I DON'T WANT ANOTHER GIRL
TO WIN IT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT WE DON'T LET
GIRLS TAKE OVER.
WE ALREADY GET OWNED
IN MARRIAGE.
PRETTY SOON WE'LL HAVE
A WOMAN PRESIDENT.
I MEAN, A GUY NEEDS TO SACK UP
AND WE NEED TO WIN THIS ONE.
>> SO BEING AN AMPUTEE, EVERY
TIME I NOTICE PEOPLE LOOKING
DOWN AT THE GROUND I THOUGHT
THEY WERE LOOKING AT MY LEG
AND MY FOOT
ABOUT WHAT ABOUT MY PANTS?
I WAS PARANOID THAT PEOPLE
WERE JUST STARING AT MY LEG.
I WAS DEFINITELY THINKING THEY
WERE SUSPECTING SOMETHING
WAS DIFFERENT.
SO I GUESS I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO JUST SHOW IT TO EVERYONE
AND SO THAT'S MY GOAL IS TO MAKE
SURE THAT I COME OUT WITH IT
AND AM ABLE TO PROVE IMMEDIATELY
THAT I AM
AS PHYSICALLY CAPABLE
AS EVERYONE ELSE.
>> I WANT TO SAY SOMETHING
TO EVERYONE.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> CAN WE GROUP?
>> GROUP MEETING, GUYS.
>> WE GOT TREE MAIL?
>> NO, NO, I KIND OF CALLED
THE GROUP MEETING.
WE ALREADY HAVE
FIRST IMPRESSIONS,
GOTTEN TO KNOW EACH OTHER
SO I THINK AT THIS POINT
I'M PRETTY COMFORTABLE
WITH MY TEAM, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
>> WAIT, I'M CONFUSED.
>> WELL...
>> PROSTHETIC.
>> I KNEW IT!
>> I KNEW IT, TOO.
>> OH!
ALL RIGHT, NOW I AM EXCITED.
(\LAUGHS\)
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I HAD A BIRTH DEFECT.
>> YOU ARE A ROCK STAR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
COOL.
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN FASCINATED
ON HOW THOSE THINGS WORK.
HOW DO YOU TELL IT TO MOVE?
(\LAUGHTER\)
>> SHE DOES HAVE A THIGH.
>> BEING THAT I'M SUCH A WUSS
I COULD ALMOST CRY.
IF I WENT TO THE FINAL THREE
WITH HER OR TWO
I'D BE LIKE JUST GIVE HER
THE MONEY.
JUST CUT HER THE CHECK BECAUSE
NO MONEY IN THE WORLD
CAN REPLACE WHAT SHE'S PROBABLY
GONE THROUGH IN HER LIFE.
BUT REALLY SHE'S GOING TO BE TOO
BIG OF A THREAT DOWN THE ROAD.
SYMPATHY VOTE NO DOUBT.
SO I FIGURE IF WE LOSE
A CHALLENGE TO THE OLD FOLKS,
SHE'S GOT TO BE ONE
OF THE FIRST ONES TO GO.
>> SO KELLY B. HAS ONE LEG
AND I DON'T WANT PEOPLE
GETTING MAD AT ME
BECAUSE I TALK ABOUT HER LEG
BUT IT'S A GAME.
FOR THE TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR
PLUS A MILLION.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO TREAT YOU
AS AN OUTCAST.
IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU CAN
OUTRUN ME, GIRL, LET'S RACE.
>> GUYS, THE FIRE,
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY.
>> THAT'S JUST...
(\APPLAUSE\)
(\RETCHING\)
>> I OVERDID IT, I THINK,
WHEN WE WERE GETTING
ALL THE WOOD AND GETTING
ALL THE BAMBOO,
AND EVERYBODY WAS SO EXCITED
TO GET HERE
AND START WORKING ON STUFF.
I JUST...
I THINK I DID MORE
THAN I NEEDED TO DO.
>> COACH NEEDS TO BE CAREFUL.
HE'S GETTING HIS ASS KICKED
OUT HERE NOW.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S GOING
FOR AN ACADEMY AWARD
OR IF HE'S GENUINELY ILL.
BUT THIS IS NOT FOR THE WEAK
AND HE'S NOT A YOUNG MAN.
>> ZERO SLEEP, SICK THROWING UP,
ANTS AND MOSQUITOS
BITING ME EVERYWHERE,
AND COLD AND SHIVERING
UNTIL THE SUN CAME UP.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER HAD
A 24-HOUR PERIOD
WHERE I WAS IN THAT MUCH
DISCOMFORT AND THAT MISERABLE.
I'VE WATCHED EVERY SECOND
OF "SURVIVOR."
I NEVER IMAGINED ANYWHERE CLOSE
THAT IT WAS THIS DIFFICULT.
FIRST TIME I'VE EVER EXPERIENCED
ANYTHING LIKE THIS
AND IT'S AN EYE OPENER,
I PROMISE YOU.
>> DID YOU KNOW JIMMY JOHNSON?
>> I DIDN'T KNOW HIM
BEFORE THIS BUT...
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> DID YOU KNOW IT WAS HIM?
>> WELL, I USED TO CHEER
FOR THE DOLPHINS SO...
I LIKE YOUR SPIRIT.
>> I LIKE YOU, TOO.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
>> I ABSOLUTELY...
I THOUGHT THAT
FROM THE BEGINNING.
EVERYTHING'S JUST...
YOU CAN MAKE AN ALLIANCE
RIGHT NOW AND THEN YOU GET
IN A CHALLENGE AND END UP
HATING THAT PERSON.
>> I DON'T THINK I'M GOING
TO HATE YOU.
>> I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT YOU
AND ME, JUST IN GENERAL.
BRENDA, SHE'S A CUTE GIRL.
I'M ATTRACTED TO HER.
I FOR SOME REASON
REALLY TRUST HER.
FIRST THOUGHT YOU COULD COME IN
AND DO...
GUYS WANT TO GET GIRLS OUT
OR SOMETHING. THAT'S CRAZY.
WHAT IF ONE OF THE GUYS IS WEAK
AND YOU DON'T WANT HIM AROUND?
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE THIS THING
WHERE I HAVE TWO DIFFERENT
ALLIANCES.
I'M NOT TRYING TO COME OUT HERE
AND LIE TO EVERYBODY
BUT MY DUMB ASS AND PUT MY NECK
ON THE LINE EARLY
AND I WAS NOT PLANNING
ON DOING THAT.
BUT I MADE THAT ALLIANCE
WITH SHANNON AND NOW I'VE GOT
TO FIGURE OUT
WHO I CAN REALLY TRUST.
>> SOMETIMES YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SAY ANYTHING.
>> I AGREE.
>> WE JUST KNOW.
I'M KIND OF USE TO HAVING GUYS
DO WHAT I SAY.
WHAT'S FUNNY IS CHASE CAME UP
AND TOLD ME THE GUYS HAVE
AN ALLIANCE GOING ON
AND OF COURSE I'M GOING TO USE
THAT INFORMATION
TO GET ME TO THE END.
I KNOW CHASE TRUSTS ME.
HE'S A REALLY NICE GUY
BUT HE'S CLUELESS.
THAT LOOKS LIKE A WELL.
YAY!
ALL RIGHT.
"THIS IS A CLUE TO A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT IS UP TO YOU
WHETHER YOU SHARE
THIS INFORMATION
WITH ANYONE ELSE.
DECIPHER THE CLUES TO FIND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL."
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> OH, GOSH, WELL, WE KEEP IT
BETWEEN US FOR SURE.
>> I THINK SO.
>> ESPECIALLY THIS EARLY.
THIS IS A MAP?
(\LAUGHS\)
I NEVER REALIZED
HOW HARD THESE ARE.
WE JUST FOUND THE CLUE
TO A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THIS EARLY IN THE GAME.
BUT WE CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
>> SO WE'RE TRYING TO DECIPHER
WHAT THE CLUES MEAN.
>> THEY'RE NOT EASY.
>> WE'RE STUMPED.
SO WE'RE THINKING WE'RE JUST
GOING TO HOLD ON TO IT
AND MAYBE COME BACK TO IT.
>> WILL YOU REMEMBER
WHERE IT IS?
>> YEAH.
>> KELLY B. AND I...
IT'S KIND OF HARD RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE WE FOUND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE
TOGETHER WHICH I WISH WE DIDN'T
FIND IT TOGETHER
SO NOW I'M KIND OF FORCED TO BE
IN AN ALLIANCE WITH HER AND I
DON'T WANT HER TO STICK AROUND
FOR A LONG TIME BECAUSE...
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO GO
TO THE END WITH HER BECAUSE,
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO SAY IT
BUT SYMPATHY VOTE FOR SURE
AND I'M NOT TRYING
TO GO UP AGAINST THAT.
>> OKAY!
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
>> TREE-MAIL!
>> "CHANGE THE COURSE
OF WATERFALLS
OR YOU MAY JUST LOSE YOUR CLAIM.
KEEP YOUR MIND IN THE GUTTER OR
BE THE FIRST TO LEAVE THE GAME."
SO CAN WE GIVE OURSELVES ANY
ADVANTAGE WITH THAT?
>> THIS IS A VERY STRESSFUL TIME
ON THESE PEOPLE.
IT'S A VERY STRESSFUL TIME
ON ME.
WE'RE THE UNDERDOGS,
THE OLDER FOLKS
AND THEY NEED MOTIVATION.
EVERYBODY IN THIS WORLD
NEEDS MOTIVATION
AND I THINK I CAN HELP
MOTIVATE THIS TEAM.
OKAY, FOLKS, TEAM HUDDLE.
FIRST OF ALL,
THE REASON WHY I'M HERE
IS I'M HERE FOR THE ADVENTURE,
BECAUSE THERE'S NO WAY
IN THE WORLD
A JURY'S GOING TO GIVE ME
A MILLION BUCKS.
I KNOW THAT.
BUT THE THING THAT I CAN DO,
I CAN HELP SOMEBODY WIN
A MILLION BUCKS.
AND THE WINNER CAN COME
FROM ONE OF YOU GUYS.
NOTHING WOULD MAKE ME HAPPIER
THAN TO SEE ONE OF YOU
WIN A MILLION BUCKS.
AND I'LL HELP YOU ALL THE WAY.
I PROMISE YOU.
JUST AS LONG AS WE'RE
PSYCHED UP FOR IT
AND WE KNOW WHAT WE'VE GOT
TO DO, WE'LL KICK THEIR ASS.
ALL RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> I JUST GOT A PEP TALK
FROM JIMMY JOHNSON!
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> WHOO!
HA!
WHOO!
HALT!
LA FLOR!
>> Jeff: OKAY.
OLDER TRIBE.
THEY CAME IN SORT OF EITHER
SERENADING YOU
OR MAYBE THAT WAS A WAR CRY.
JIMMY?
ANY IMPACT?
>> I REALLY DON'T CONCENTRATE
ON WHAT THEY DO.
WE KNOW WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
>> Jeff: JUD, WHAT DO YOU MAKE
OF THE OLDER TRIBE?
>> JEFF, HIS NAME IS FABIO,
NOT JUDSON.
HIS NAME IS FABIO.
HE'S THE MAN.
>> Jeff: LET'S FIGURE OUT.
KELLY, ARE YOU GOING TO GO BY
KELLY IN PURPLE AND BLOND HAIR?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING BY?
>> PURPLE KELLY.
>> Jeff: PURPLE KELLY.
ALL RIGHT.
TYRONE, WHEN YOU SEE SOMEBODY
ON THE OTHER TRIBE
LIKE KELLY WITH ONE
ARTIFICIAL LEG,
DOES THAT MAKE YOU THINK
"I'VE GOT TO TAKE IT
A LITTLE EASIER ON HER"?
>> NOT AT ALL.
THIS IS A COMPETITION,
WE'RE ALL OPERATING
BIG THE SAME RULES
AND WE'RE GOING TO WIN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
FOR TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
ONE PERSON WILL BE AT THE TOP
OF A TOWER POURING WATER
WHILE FIVE OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL USE SECTIONS OF GUTTER TO
DIRECT THAT WATER INTO A BARREL.
ONCE THE BARREL FILLS, A LARGE
BAG OF PUZZLE PIECES WILL DROP.
THE FOUR REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS
MUST THEN USE THOSE PIECES
TO SOLVE THE PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT
WINS IMMUNITY.
(\APPLAUSE\)
IF YOU HAVE IMMUNITY
IN YOUR POSSESSION,
YOU CAN NOT BE SENT HOME.
THE LOSERS OF THIS CHALLENGE
WILL GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE THE FIRST PERSON
WILL BE VOTED OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW TO THE MEDALLION OF POWER.
OLDER TRIBE, YOU GUYS HAVE
THIS MEDALLION,
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF POWER IT POSSESSES.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS:
THE MEDALLION OF POWER
GIVES YOU HUGE ADVANTAGE
AT CHALLENGES.
IF YOU USE IT TODAY,
YOU WILL START THIS CHALLENGE
WITH ONE BUCKET OF WATER
ALREADY IN YOUR BARREL.
GIVEN THAT IT TAKES
ABOUT FIVE BUCKETS TO FILL,
THIS IS A SIGNIFICANT ADVANTAGE.
IF YOU USE IT,
THEN THE MEDALLION GOES
TO THE YOUNGER TRIBE AND THEY
WILL HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY
TO USE IT AT THE NEXT CHALLENGE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S ENOUGH.
>> THIS TYPE OF A CHALLENGE
WE CAN COMPETE WITH THEM
NO PROBLEM.
>> LET'S MAKE A STATEMENT.
LET'S MAKE A STATEMENT
AND HOLD ON TO IT.
>> SO WE'RE KEEPING IT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE,
WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE?
YOU GOING TO USE IT OR NOT?
>> WE'RE GOING TO KEEP IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
OLDER TRIBE OPTING TO KEEP
THE MEDALLION OF POWER.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
OKAY.
IT IS THE FIRST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
IN "SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA,"
OLD VERSUS YOUNG.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> SET IT UP!
SET IT UP!
>> Jeff: THE TASK
IS VERY SIMPLE:
ONE PERSON POURS WATER DOWN
THE GUTTERS INTO THE BARREL.
ONCE YOUR BARREL IS FULL,
THE PUZZLES WILL DROP.
>> GO, BABY!
GO!
>> DON'T SPILL IT!
>> VERY CLOSE!
VERY CLOSE.
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT, GUYS,
KEEP IT STEADY!
>> FAST!
FAST!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE
HAS A NICE FLOW.
>> SLOW AND STEADY!
DON'T WASTE IT!
>> JUST LIKE THAT.
LITTLE SLOWER.
>> I GOT IT.
>> SLOW AND STEADY,
EVERYTHING YOU CAN GET.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
A STEADY FLOW.
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE
WITH A GREAT FLOW.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
KEEP IT GOING!
WHOO!
>> COME ON, HOLLY!
>> KEEP IT GOING!
>> KEEP IT GOING, KEEP IT GOING!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE RELEASES
THEIR PUZZLE PIECES.
>> LET'S GO, GIRLS,
KEEP IT GOING!
DON'T PANIC!
>> GO, GO!
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE RELEASED
THEIR PUZZLE PIECES.
>> LET'S GO!
>> YOU GOT IT LADIES!
LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES WORKING
ON THEIR PUZZLE.
WE ARE VERY EVEN
IN THIS FIRST CHALLENGE.
IT'S GOING TO COME DOWN TO FOUR
OLDER WOMEN, FOUR YOUNGER WOMEN.
WILL IT BE WISDOM OR ENTHUSIASM
THAT WILL WIN THIS CHALLENGE?
>> LOOK AT THE BUFF, GUYS!
>> Jeff: YOUNG TRIBE OFF
TO A QUICK START.
>> LOOK AT THE BUFF!
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE NOW
GETTING SOMETHING GOING.
OLDER TRIBE,
YOU NEED TO PICK IT UP!
>> COME ON!
>> ALMOST THERE!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE GETTING
VERY CLOSE!
WHAT'S NOT RIGHT?
SOMETHING'S NOT WORKING.
>> LEAVE THAT!
>> Jeff: OLDER TRIBE NOW
BACK IN IT.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT!
>> FIT IT IN!
>> Jeff: YOUNGER TRIBE WINS
IMMUNITY!
(\CHEERS AND APPLAUSE\)
YOUNGER TRIBE, CONGRATULATIONS.
(\APPLAUSE\)
NOBODY GOING HOME
FROM THE YOUNGER TRIBE.
BRENDA, WOULD YOU HAVE USED
THAT MEDALLION OF POWER?
>> YES, DEFINITELY.
BECAUSE YOU'RE HERE TO WIN,
SO WHY TAKE CHANCES WHEN YOU'RE
HERE DOING IT RIGHT NOW?
WHY ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT
TOMORROW OR THE NEXT DAY
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING RIGHT NOW?
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
OLDER TRIBE, I'LL SEE YOU
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD ON
BACK TO CAMP.
>> I REMEMBER MY SECOND
SUPERBOWL
WE LOST THE FIRST TWO
BALL GAMES.
BUT WE WERE ABLE TO KEEP GOING
AND WE HUNG IN THERE
AND, OF COURSE,
WON THE SUPER BOWL.
LOSING THE FIRST CHALLENGE,
IT'S NOT THE END OF THE WORLD.
JUST MAKE SURE WE MAKE
A SMART DECISION,
GET RID OF THE WEAKEST PLAYER
AND STILL HAVE THE MEDALLION,
STILL HAVE A STRONG TEAM.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
I DON'T KNOW, I CAN'T EVEN THINK
CLEARLY RIGHT NOW.
I'M JUNKED FROM THE TRAUMA
OF THE CHALLENGE.
I NEED TO SLEEP.
I WANT TO LAY DOWN.
I'M 48 YEARS OLD, BUT THIS PLACE
ALREADY KNOCKED ME DOWN,
IT'S ONLY DAY THREE.
SO I'VE GOT TO LEARN TO DEAL
WITH THAT
AND I'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> JIMMY T.,
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I THINK JIMMY'S TRYING
TO HORN SWAGGLE EVERYBODY,
TELLING EVERYBODY I REALLY CARE
ABOUT YOU,
I WANT TO MAKE YOU
A MILLION DOLLARS.
SO ANYWAY, I'M VOTING
JIMMY TONIGHT.
I'M JUST...
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I'VE GOT TO SAY THIS.
I'M NOT GOING
TO NOT BE HEARD HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M NOT GOING
TO NOT BE HEARD.
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
I'M LISTENING, I'M LISTENING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I KNOW...
I KNOW THAT SOMETIMES
STARS BLIND PEOPLE.
>> OKAY.
I'M TOTALLY WITH YOU.
>> I'VE GOT TO CALL HIM DOWN.
>> NOBODY WANTS TO BE
THE FIRST ONE TO GO HOME.
>> WHOEVER IT IS, YOU KNOW,
WE ALL GOT TO DECIDE TO TAKE OUT
THE WEAKEST PLAYER.
AND THAT MAKES THE TEAM
STRONGER.
>> SO WHO DO YOU THINK
IS THE WEAKEST PLAYER?
>> I THINK IT'S EITHER MYSELF
OR WENDY.
PERSONALLY I THINK IT'S WENDY.
I MEAN, HOW IS THIS TEAM
GOING TO GET STRONGER?
FORGET ABOUT PERSONALITIES.
FORGET ABOUT ALLIANCES.
>> YOU REALLY MEAN THAT?
>> I REALLY DO.
I MEAN IT.
>> COACH EXPLAINED THAT WE NEED
TO KEEP OUR TEAM STRONGER
AND I AGREE WITH HIM.
AND THAT'S SOMETHING
I SHOULD HAVE THOUGHT ABOUT
BEFORE I RUSHED INTO
THE ALLIANCE WITH WENDY.
>> THIS GAME WE JUST DON'T KNOW.
>> I MEAN, BUT YOU ASK YOURSELF,
DOES THE TEAM GET STRONGER
WITHOUT WENDY?
>> I'M REALLY CAUGHT
IN A DILEMMA
BECAUSE I SHOOK HER HAND
AND GAVE HER MY WORD.
SO I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST GOING TO SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> HERE'S THE QUESTION,
THOUGH...
>> AND THE POT'S NOT
GOING TO SET WELL.
>> I LOOK NERVOUS AND CONCERNED
PROBABLY BECAUSE I AM NERVOUS
AND CONCERNED.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW IF I'M
NERVOUS BUT I'M CONCERNED
BECAUSE I THINK I'M ON THE OUTS
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
I DEVELOPED A BOND
WITH A LOT OF THE PEOPLE.
>> YOU GOING TO COME OUT?
>> NO, I'M GOING TO GO BACK UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU SHOULDN'T TRUST ANYONE
IN "SURVIVOR" THAT'S TRUE.
HOLLY WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME AND
SHE TOLD ME...
WE SHOOK ON AN ALLIANCE THE
FIRST DAY.
SO I'M THINKING HECK, WHAT'S
GOING ON IS ALL I WANT TO KNOW.
>> HERE'S WHAT JIMMY SAID TO ME.
HE SAID AT THIS POINT IN THE
BALL GAME WE SHOULD FOCUS
ON STRENGTH AND ALLIANCES
ARE BROKEN ALL THE TIME.
HE SAID THERE'S
TWO WEAK PLAYERS.
>> DID HE INCLUDE HIMSELF
IN THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> THE OTHER?
>> WENDY.
>> SO WHO DO YOU THINK
KEEPS THIS IS TRIBE STRONG?
>> I'M NOT... I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU...
I DON'T KNOW AT THIS POINT
WHAT TO THINK.
>> I DON'T THINK EITHER ONE
OF THEM IS A BAD CHOICE.
>> UM...
>> WHY DON'T WE
GO AROUND THE CIRCLE
AND HONESTLY SAY
WHO YOU WOULD RATHER.
DOES THAT SOUND FAIR?
>> YEAH.
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
>> SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> THIS IS WHAT I THINK.
I'M OF THE OPINION THAT WE NEED
TO KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG...
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
THAT WE'VE HAD TO REALLY
FEEL EACH OTHER OUT
FOR SOMETHING AS IMPORTANT
AS WHO'S GOING TO GO HOME
AND YOU TRY TO COAX IT OUT
OF PEOPLE,
YOU'RE GETTING TENTATIVENESS,
NERVOUSNESS ABOUT ANYBODY
SAYING A NAME.
>> SO WHAT DO WE SAY?
I DON'T KNOW?
>> UM...
>> IT COULD BE A REAL TOSS
BETWEEN WENDY JO
AND JIMMY JOHNSON.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW EITHER ONE
COULD REALLY PERFORM
IN A PHYSICAL CHALLENGE.
WE'RE MAKING SOME HUNCHES HERE.
WE'RE MAKING SOME GUESSES
AND WENDY JO PROBABLY DOESN'T
ADD A LOT ON THE PHYSICALITY
SIDE OF THE CHALLENGES.
AND I THINK JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
JIMMY JOHNSON
AND YOU'RE TELLING ME THE JURY'S
NOT GOING TO GIVE YOU
THE MILLION DOLLARS,
I'M NOT BUYING IT.
IT WILL BE INTERESTING.
WE WILL HAVE TO SEE JUST HOW
THIS THING PLAYS OUT.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU
IS A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB THE TORCH
AND APPROACH THE FLAME.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
BECAUSE IN THIS GAME
FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE FIRE,
YOU'RE STILL IN THE GAME.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE,
SO ARE YOU.
WELL, WELCOME TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
FIRST IMPRESSIONS.
JANE, WHAT IS TYPICALLY
THE FIRST IMPRESSION
PEOPLE HAVE WHEN THEY MEET YOU?
>> THEY MIGHT CALL ME
A SOUTHERN HILLBILLY.
>> I CALL HER "SURVIVOR"
McGUYVER BECAUSE WITHIN AN HOUR
OF HITTING THE BEACH
JANE HAD THE FIRE GOING.
SHE CAN DO ANYTHING HERE.
>> Jeff: JANE, DID YOU KNOW
YOU COULD DO IT?
>> HELL, YEAH,
I KNEW I COULD DO IT.
BECAUSE I SAW AN ARTICLE
THAT YOU WROTE AND IT SAID
"WHY WOULD ANYBODY COME
AND PLAY 'SURVIVOR'
THAT DIDN'T KNOW
HOW TO MAKE A FIRE?"
>> Jeff: YOU LISTENED
TO SOMETHING I SAID?
>> I TOOK IT TO HEART, TOO,
BECAUSE I PRACTICED
FOR TWO MONTHS.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T.,
HOW BIG WERE THOSE
FIRST FEW MOMENTS FOR YOU
IN MAKING FIRST IMPRESSIONS?
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
WHERE I DO COME FROM
I'M A LEADER.
WHEN I TALK, PEOPLE LISTEN.
WHEN YOU GET TO "SURVIVOR",
THERE'S PEOPLE THAT ARE
STRONGER,
THERE'S PEOPLE WITH MORE
INTEGRITY AND WHEN YOU HAVE
ONE OF THE GREATEST LEADERS
IN THE N.F.L.
OF ALL TIME,
IT'S VERY FRUSTRATING.
I'M JUST ANOTHER PLAYER HERE.
>> Jeff: JIMMY, WHEN YOU HEAR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
DO YOU FEEL A LITTLE TARGET
ON YOUR BACK
THAT PEOPLE WILL EITHER LOOK
TO YOU FOR LEADERSHIP
OR BE ANNOYED
THAT YOU ARE A LEADER?
>> LET ME MAKE IT CLEAR,
I'M NOT THE BOSS.
BUT, YEAH, I'M GOING TO BE
A TARGET EVERY SINGLE
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I KNOW THAT.
BUT I'M NOT A THREAT TO ANYBODY
HERE FOR THE SIMPLE REASON
NO JURY'S GOING TO AWARD ME
A MILLION BUCKS.
I KNOW THAT.
I'M NOT HERE FOR THE MONEY,
I'M HERE FOR THE ADVENTURE.
BUT I'LL ONLY BE HERE AS LONG
AS I CAN HELP THIS TEAM
BE SUCCESSFUL.
>> Jeff: JIMMY T,
CAN YOU BUY THAT?
>> NO WAY, HE'S GOING TO TRY
TO WIN THIS THING.
AND I THINK HE CAN WIN THE GAME
BECAUSE IF HE LEADS SO WELL
AND DESERVES TO WIN THE GAME,
THE JURY'S GOING TO LET HIM
WIN THAT GAME.
>> Jeff: MARTY, JIMMY T.
BRINGS UP AN INTERESTING POINT.
MOST PEOPLE ON "SURVIVOR"
ARE BORN LEADERS.
IS THAT A SHOCK FOR YOU
TO GET USED TO AS WELL?
>> I THINK COMING INTO IT
YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
ABOUT BEING OVER-THE-TOP LEADER
BECAUSE TYPICALLY
THAT PUTS A TARGET
ON YOUR BACK RIGHT AWAY.
SO I THINK THERE'S DIFFERENT
WAYS TO LEAD
AND IT'S MAKING SURE
YOU DON'T LEAD
IN THE WAY
THAT GETS YOU INTO TROUBLE.
>> Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT
TONIGHT'S VOTE.
WHO HERE BY A SHOW OF HANDS
TRULY THINKS THEY'RE IN TROUBLE?
MORE THAN HALF THE TRIBE.
HOLLY, WHY ARE YOU CONCERNED
IT MIGHT BE YOU TONIGHT?
>> I MADE AN ALLIANCE
RIGHT INTO THE GAME
AND COACH CAME OVER TO ME
AFTER THE CHALLENGE
AND HE FEELS LIKE THERE'S
TWO WEAK LINKS.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW IF I
NECESSARILY AGREE
WITH WHO HE DECIDES.
SO DEFINITELY.
>> Jeff: WENDY,
WHY DO YOU THINK THE TRIBE
WOULD WANT TO VOTE YOU OUT
TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE I CONNECTED
VERY WELL WITH THE PEOPLE HERE.
I WAS VERY BUSY BUT SOME PEOPLE
TALKED AT THE CAMP
AND I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE
I GOT A LOT OF THAT.
BECAUSE THEY WOULD BE QUITE
SURPRISED
IF SOMEONE ASKED ME
SOME QUESTIONS.
THERE'S NOBODY HERE
THAT EVEN KNOWS MY AGE.
NOT ONE PERSON ASKED ME.
>> I ASKED YOU.
>> NO, YOU DIDN'T.
>> THAT'S ONE QUESTION
I NEVER ASK ANYONE.
>> NO, YOU NEVER ASKED ME!
>> YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO ASK
A WOMAN HER AGE.
>> HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> 48.
>> YOU LOOK SO YOUNG.
>> Jeff: WENDY, TYPICALLY
THE ONE QUESTION
YOU WOULDN'T ASK A WOMAN
IS "HOW OLD ARE YOU."
SO IT'S INTERESTING THAT THAT'S
THE QUESTION
THAT HAS YOU TWEAKED.
>> OH, IT DOESN'T
HAVE ME TWEAKED,
I JUST FOUND IT INTERESTING
THAT NOBODY ASKED ME.
MAYBE I'LL START
TOOTING MY HORN.
(\LAUGHS\)
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT I SHOULD DO.
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
TALKATIVE AND SHARE EVERYTHING.
BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO COME IN
TALK, TALK, TALK,
AND DRIVE PEOPLE CRAZY
BECAUSE PEOPLE DON'T LIKE PEOPLE
WHO TALK ALL THE TIME.
SO I STAYED PRETTY QUIET
AND THAT IS NOT ME.
I HAVE A NICKNAME
OF CHATTER BOX.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JANE, YOU'RE UP.
>> CAN I SAY ONE THING?
>> Jeff: WENDY, YOU HAD
SOMETHING ELSE
YOU WANTED TO SAY?
>> I WOULD ALSO LIKE TO TELL
THE GROUP I THINK THERE'S A LOT
THAT I CAN BRING THROUGH
MY STRENGTH, MY LEADERSHIP.
I COULD BE VERY FRIENDLY,
VERY HONEST, VERY FUNNY,
FUN TO BE WITH, STRONG WILLED,
STRONG PHYSICALLY.
PEOPLE LIKE TO BE MY FRIEND.
PEOPLE LIKE TO BE WITH ME.
THEY TRUST ME ALL THE TIME.
TRUST IS IMPORTANT.
AND I DON'T HAVE ANY BLISTERS
ON MY FEET AND THAT'S AN ASSET.
THAT WILL HELP, JUST A LITTLE
THING I'D POINT OUT.
I THINK THAT'S ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: I JUST WANT
TO MAKE SURE
YOU GET EVERYTHING
OFF YOUR CHEST.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO THE VOTE.
JANE, YOU'RE UP.
>> INITIALLY THE DECISION
WAS TOUGH BUT AFTER HEARING
YOU SPEAK TONIGHT WITH YOUR
EXCUSES, IT BECAME EASY.
WENDY JO, YOU GOTTA GO.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, WENDY.
EVE.
THAT'S ONE VOTE EVE,
ONE VOTE WENDY.
WENDY.
TWO VOTES WENDY.
THAT'S THREE VOTES WENDY.
WENDY, THAT'S FOUR VOTES WENDY.
WENDY, THAT'S FIVE VOTES WENDY,
ONE VOTE EVE.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA," WENDY.
THAT'S SIX, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: WENDY, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT'S VOTE
WAS CLEARLY DESIGNED
TO IMPROVE THE CHEMISTRY
OF THIS TRIBE.
ONE GOOD THING ABOUT COMING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
YOU WILL LEAVE HERE WITH FIRE.
HERE'S YOUR FLINT.
GRAB A TORCH, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME
ON "SURVIVOR."
>> FATIGUE MAKES
THE MINDS GET WEAK.
>> NEW YORK CITY BOY DANNY,
LET'S JUST FILL HIS SHOES UP
AND THEN...
>> WHY YOU RAISING
YOUR VOICE AT ME?
I CAN GET LOUD, TOO.
I DON'T LIKE ANYTHING ABOUT HIM.
HE GETS ON MY NERVES.
>> Jeff: 21 SEASONS
OF "SURVIVOR,"
NEVER HAD AN OPENING QUESTION
OPEN THAT MUCH WHOOP ASS.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR.
AND WHAT I FIND INTERESTING
IS THIS IS PROBABLY
THE ONLY TIME IN MY LIFE
I WAS A LOSER WITH STRANGERS.
I CHANGED COMING INTO THE GAME.
IF I WOULD HAVE BEEN MYSELF IT
WOULD HAVE WORKED OUT BETTER.
I WISH I COULD GO BACK.
MAYBE THEY'LL STICK ME
ON THE YOUNG PEOPLE'S TRIBE.