>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
AFTER 18 DAYS, RECENT EVENTS
CENTERED ON THREE PEOPLE--
NAONKA, SHE WAS AN ANGRY
AND VINDICTIVE TRIBEMATE.
>> WHY ARE YOU RAISING YOUR
VOICE AT ME?
I CAN GET LOUD, TOO.
>> Jeff: SHE HAD A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL
AND CONTROL OF THE ENTIRE ESPADA
TRIBE.
NAONKA AND HER ALLY CHASE HAD
DECIDED
ALINA WAS THE NEXT TO GO.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW
YOU GONNA BE WALKING AWAY
AND YOUR TORCH IS PUT OUT.
MARTY, BEFORE THE SWITCH, HE WAS
THE MOST POWERFUL
AND OUTSPOKEN PLAYER ON HIS
TRIBE.
>> DO NOT MESS AROUND WITH ME.
I MEAN, I'M PLAYING THIS GAME
FOR REAL.
>> Jeff: AFTER THE SWITCH, HE
WAS FIGHTING
FOR HIS LIFE ON THE LA FLOR
TRIBE.
HIS BIGGEST ENEMY WAS JANE.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL I HOPE
MARTY GOES HOME.
>> Jeff: MARTY HAD ONLY ONE ALLY
JILL, AND ONE WEAPON--
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AND THEN
THERE'S SASH.
SASH HAD BECOME THE PUPPET
MASTER AT LA FLOR.
>> WHO STAYS IN THIS GAME IT'S
ABOUT HOW LOYAL ARE YOU TO ME.
>> Jeff: ESPADA WINS IMMUNITY!
AFTER LA FLOR LOST THE LAST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
SASH CONVINCED MARTY TO GIVE UP
HIS HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
IN EXCHANGE FOR MORE LIFE IN THE
GAME.
>> IF WE LOSE THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE,
I'LL GIVE THE IDOL BACK TO YOU.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL MARTY
WAS AMAZED
SASH KEPT HIS WORD AND SENT JILL
HOME INSTEAD.
JILL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW MARTY IS LEFT COMPLETELY
ALONE
WITH NO FRIENDS AND NO IDOL.
12 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> THE VULTURES ARE DEFINITELY
CIRCLING
AND IT'S DEAD MAN WALKING.
IT'S DAY 19, AND I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS GAME HAS PUT ME WHERE I'M
AT RIGHT NOW.
LAST NIGHT SUCKED.
JILL WAS AN INCREDIBLE PLAYER, A
GREAT CONTENDER,
A LOVER OF THE GAME, AND THERE
ARE SOME PEOPLE LEFT
I THINK HAVE NO RIGHT TO BE IN
THIS GAME.
SO HAVING NO JILL, NO IDOL, IS
TOTAL EXPOSURE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE THE NEXT
PERSON TO GO FROM "SURVIVOR."
I JUST HAVE TO DO THE BEST THAT
I CAN AND HANG ON.
>> GUYS!
>> WHAT HAVE WE GOT?
>> UNCLE FABIO FOUND SOME TREE
MAIL!
LET'S READ IT FIRST.
LET'S READ IT.
>> I THINK I SEE IT!
>> IT'S LIKE A MAP.
>> WHO WANTS TO HOLD THE KEY?
>> OH!
>> "LA FLOR PACK UP ALL THE
BELONGINGS YOU WILL NEED
FOR THE DURATION OF YOUR STAY
HERE ON THE ISLAND
AND FOLLOW THIS MAP TO YOUR NEW
HOME."
>> MERGE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I THINK I'M GOING TO CRY
RIGHT NOW.
>> COULDN'T HAVE BEEN BETTER
NEWS FOR ME
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
THE TRIBES GETTING TOGETHER SIX
ON SIX I THINK IS GOING
TO BE MOSTLY A LA FLOR JOCKEYING
AROUND.
THESE GUYS ARE GOING
TO BE WANTED TO OFF ONE OF THEIR
OWN FOR SURE.
THERE WAS DIVISION BEFORE,
NAONKA, AND ALINA,
THEY COULD BE IN TROUBLE.
I'M ECSTATIC, MAN.
I'M BACK IN THE SADDLE AGAIN.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, LA FLOR!
>> THAT'S A BIG OLD CHEST.
>> ESPADA, DO NOT OPEN THIS BOX
UNTIL YOU HAVE THE KEY.
>> THEY HAVE THE KEY.
>> MAKE ROOM AT YOUR CAMP.
COMPANY WILL BE ARRIVING SOON.
>> THE MERGE?
>> THE MERGE.
>> HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> AT ESPADA?
>> WOW.
>> STAYING HERE?
GET A FIRE GOING AND WAIT FOR
THEM, I GUESS.
>> WE NEED TO DECIDE WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO
SO THAT WE CAN KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
>> I DON'T KNOW, NOW THAT IT'S
BECOMING MORE
OF AN INDIVIDUAL GAME AND PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO START FENDING
FOR THEMSELVES, I THINK I NEED
TO DO THE SAME.
ALINA, YOU CAN SEE RIGHT THROUGH
HER.
SHE BURNED SOME BRIDGES EARLY ON
THE IN GAME
AND SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO GO HOME
NEXT WHEN WE WERE
THE ORIGINAL LA FLOR, SO SHE'S
DEFINITELY OUTLASTED
HER EXPECTED TIME IN THIS GAME
AND I THINK EVERYBODY AGREES
IT'S TIME FOR HER TO GO HOME.
>> LIKE, WE CAN GET TO FINAL SIX
IF THE SIX OF US STAY STRONG.
IF NOBODY PUSHES US ASIDE
THE SIX OF US CAN TOTALLY DO IT.
MARTY IS STILL HERE.
MARTY WILL BE OUR BIGGEST THREAT
IN THE GAME
AND THAT MEANS HE HAS TO GO
FIRST.
>> AND HE HAS AN IDOL.
>> AND HE HAS AN IDOL SO THAT
MEANS WE HAVE
TO DO A MAJOR BLIND-SIDE.
AS LONG AS HE DOESN'T GET
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY--
LET'S MAKE SURE THAT DOESN'T
HAPPEN, GUYS--
AND THEN WE GET RID OF THE HEAD
HONCHO.
>> NOBODY WAS REALLY ON BOARD
WITH ALINA'S PLAN AT ALL,
NOT EVEN UNCLE DAN.
ALINA IS IN THIS PLAN BY HERSELF
THE ONE-WOMAN ARMY,
WITHOUT KNOWING SHE'S GOING TO
BE THE FIRST ONE OUT
IF SHE DOESN'T GET THE IMMUNITY
FIRST.
SHE CAN BE G.I.
JANE ALL SHE WANTS BUT SHE WILL
BE G.I. JANE ALL BY HERSELF WITH
NO ARMY, NOBODY BEHIND HER.
>> HERE THEY ARE, GUYS.
>> WHO'S GONE?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE JILL'S GONE?
>> JILL.
JILL'S GONE.
>> WE THOUGHT THAT MARTY AND
JILL WERE
SUPER STRONG OVER THERE.
WE THOUGHT THEY WERE, LIKE,
RUNNING THINGS
AND IT TELLS US A LOT THAT JILL
WAS VOTED OUT.
>> THIS IS THE COMPANY WE WERE
EXPECTING.
>> WELCOME BACK.
>> COMING BACK TO CAMP WAS LIKE
REBIRTH.
IT REALLY FELT LIKE HOME, SWEET
HOME.
AND I FELT LIKE THE GAME IS
STARTING ALL OVER AGAIN,
AND I'VE BEEN GIVEN A NEW LEASE
ON LIFE.
>> SHOULD WE GO SEE WHAT'S IN
THE CHEST?
>> LET'S GO OPEN THE CHEST!
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OPEN IT UP.
(\CHEERS\)
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> BREAD, BREAD, BREAD!
>> LA FLOR AND ESPADA, REPLACE
YOUR OLD BUFFS
WITH THESE NEW ONES.
YOU HAVE MERGED.
COME UP WITH A NEW TRIBE NAME
AND BEGIN THE NEXT PHASE OF YOUR
ADVENTURE.
GOOD LUCK, ENJOY THE GIFTS.
YOU HAVE EARNED THEM.
(\CHEERS\)
>> WE MADE IT TO THE MERGE!
AND WE'RE GOING TO FEAST!
YOU KNOW, WE'RE MERGING!
OH!
I'M DIGGING THE RED BUFFS.
>> I THOUGHT OF A NAME FOR THE
NEW TRIBE, "LIBERTAD."
WHICH IS FREEDOM, LIBERTY.
I KIND OF DIG THAT I GOT TO
OFFER THE NEW NAME.
"LIBERTAD" REALLY RESONATED FOR
ME PERSONALLY.
IT MEANS LIBERTY, AND IN THIS
CASE, IT CAN ALSO MEAN FREEDOM,
FREEDOM FROM EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENED UP TO THIS POINT,
AND IT'S A NEW START.
>> LET'S GET BACK TO CAMP.
>> YES, OH, MAN.
WE HAVE TO DRINK ALL OF THIS
TODAY!
>> EVERYBODY GRAB A COOKIE.
>> LIBERTAD!
>> WHEN WE FINALLY OPENED THE
TREASURE CHEST,
THAT FOOD WAS YUMMY TO MY TUMMY.
THE SALAMI, I THINK IT JUST
DISSOLVED IN MY MOUTH.
IT WAS SO GOOD.
LIKE MY BOOTY?
(\FARTS\)
I EVEN SNUCK SOME NUTS TO PUT IN
MY BRA.
I WAS GETTING IT ALL, HONEY, ALL
OF IT.
I PROBABLY STILL HAVE SOME
PEANUTS IN MY-- IN MY POCKET.
>> WOW!
>> YEAH, NOW YOU'LL GIVE ME A
HUG.
NOW THAT WE'RE ALL FAT AND
HAPPY.
>> SEEING NAONKA AGAIN WAS THE
BEST
BECAUSE I FELT LIKE, WOW, SHE'S
REAL, SUCH A RELIEF.
I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T HAVE TO
SECOND GUESS HER AT ALL.
>> SHE ALREADY IS.
WE NEED TO TAKE A WALK.
>> YEAH.
>> TO KNOW THAT WE'RE BACK IN
THE GAME TOGETHER
FEELS REALLY GOOD.
KEEP IN MIND, ONLY THE PERSON
THAT DON'T HAVE NO ALLIANCE,
SO BE CAREFUL OF HER.
SHE'S GOING TO BE WATCHING YOU.
>> ME AND NAONKA TALKED ABOUT
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED.
SHE TALKED ABOUT HOW ALINA HAS
BEEN SO SHADY.
I DON'T KNOW, I TOLD HER
EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED ON THE OTHER SIDE.
THEY TREATED JANE REALLY BAD AND
I STOOD UP FOR HER.
I DON'T KNOW, EVERYBODY OVER
HERE THOUGHT
SHE WAS HOOKING UP WITH MARTY.
>> REALLY?
>> INCLUDING ME.
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE.
MAYBE MARTY IS SMART AND HE'S
STRONG
BUT IT SEEMED LIKE HE WAS
GUNNING.
>> I TOLD HER EVERYTHING.
SHE KNOWS WITH ME IT'S 100%.
SO SASH CAME UP WITH A BRILLIANT
IDEA TO ASK HIM FOR THE IDOL,
TO GIVE IT TO SASH.
>> DOES SASH HAVE IT?
>> SASH HAS THE IDOL.
>> OH!
GET OUT OF HERE!
>> HE DID IT.
>> BRENDA, THE ONE THAT WAS WITH
ME AND I FOUND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, SASH
ASKED MARTY FOR
AND IT HE GAVE IT TO HIM.
THE SOONER WE GET
ALINA AND MARTY OUT
THE SMOOTHER THE GAME WILL GO.
>> WE'LL BE ABLE TO KNOCK THEM
OUT ONE BY ONE BY ONE BY ONE.
>> THIS IS GOING TO GET REAL
WEIRD.
>> THIS IS GOING TO GET WICKED.
>> I'M DEAD SERIOUS.
>> I LOVE THE STATE OF GEORGIA,
REALLY.
>> WE'VE GOT A CREEK BELOW OUR
HOUSE.
68 STEPS TO GO DOWN THERE.
I WAS RUNNING THAT 10 TIMES A
DAY GETTING IN SHAPE FOR THIS,
RUNNING THREE MILES A DAY AND
SWIMMING, TOO.
>> YOU SEEM LIKE A REAL COOL
LADY.
>> HONEY, YOU CAN STAY AT MY
HOUSE ANY TIME.
EVEN IF I'M NOT THERE, THE DOOR
IS ALREADY OPEN.
GOT TURKEYS, GOT A DOG THAT
LIVES IN THE YARD.
I FEEL VERY SAFE PLUS I HAVE A
SHOTGUN, A .22.
>> JANE AND I CLICKED RIGHT
AWAY.
SHE'S A GOOD, OLD LADY.
SHE'S AN AWESOME LADY.
SHE TALKS WITH A TWANG.
SHE REMINDS ME AT HOME.
I MISS MY HOME.
I MISS MY MOTHER.
HER AND I CAN CONNECT VERY WELL.
>> THEY TREATED ME LIKE I WAS
THE UGLY DUCKLING OVER HERE
BECAUSE I HAD A SOUTHERN ACCENT
AND I'M A RED NECK.
>> I HAD NO IDEA YOU WERE SO
BAD.
I LOVE A NORTH CAROLINA GIRL.
PEOPLE NEED TO STICK TOGETHER.
>> AND I KNEW RIGHT THEN AND
THERE,
YOU'RE A NORTH CAROLINA BOY, I'M
A NORTH CAROLINA GIRL,
WE'RE GOING TO HIT IT OFF REALLY
GOOD.
AND I WAS TALKING TO CHASE ABOUT
HIS DAD PASSING
AND MY HUSBAND PASSING, SO I'VE
GOT A CONNECTION WITH HIM,
WITH CHASE.
>> WHAT ARE WE DOING?
BREAKFAST, HUH?
>> DON'T TAKE A BIG ASS BITE,
EITHER.
>> HEY, IS THIS COOL?
NAONKA?
>> I GUESS, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S DAY 20, WE DON'T HAVE A LOT
OF FOOD LEFT AND I WOKE UP
THIS MORNING VERY IRRITABLE.
IT WAS MY IDEA TO MAKE THE
TORTILLAS AND THE FACT
THAT I'M THE LAST TO GET
EVERYTHING
AND I GET THE SMALLEST TORTILLA.
OKAY, YOU GUYS WANT TO PLAY.
I CAN PLAY, TOO.
>> DON'T TAKE A BIG BITE, FABIO.
>> I JUST WANTED IT TEST IT OUT
YOU KNOW.
>> THIS MORNING, AFTER WE WERE
DONE EATING BREAKFAST,
NA TOOK THE FLOUR AND PUT IT IN
HER BAG,
AND SHE GOT UP AND SHE WALKED
OUT OF CAMP.
AND I THOUGHT THAT WAS A LITTLE
STRANGE.
WHY DID SHE JUST TAKE THE FLOUR?
>> I'M HIDING THE FLOUR BECAUSE
THOSE TORTILLAS WERE GOOD
AND EVERYBODY WAS BEING STINGY
AND I PUT A LOT OF MY HEART
AND SOUL INTO MAKING THOSE
THINGS AND I MADE A BIG ONE
FOR ME AND THEY ALL TOOK IT.
THEY REALLY MADE ME MAD.
SO I'M GOING TO MAKE THEM MAD.
DON'T PLAY WITH ME IN THIS GAME.
I CAN PLAY DIRTY.
I AM STEALING EQUIPMENT TO MAKE
TORTILLAS, AND I'M TAKING FRUIT.
I'VE TAKEN BOWLS AND SPOONS.
IT TASTES BETTER WHEN YOU'RE
STEALING IT.
IT'S LIKE A SWEET VICTORY.
ALINA, EVERYBODY IS AGAINST HER
RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T MIND BEING THAT ONE
PERSON THAT, YOU KNOW,
TELLS HER A LITTLE
SOMETHING-SOMETHING.
>> SO WHERE DO YOU STAND?
DO YOU STAND WITH THE SIX WE
TALKED ABOUT
OR ARE YOU BACK WITH BRENDA?
>> I'M WITH THE SIX.
>> IF ANYBODY I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT IS YOU.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
BACK WITH BRENDA.
I MEAN, YOU SPENT ALL DAY WITH
HER YESTERDAY.
>> I WAS CATCHING UP WITH HER.
>> DO YOU THINK THE FIRST VOTE
WILL STILL BE MARTY?
>> KELLY IS RIGHT THERE.
I'LL TELL YOU RIGHT NOW, THEY'RE
GUNNING FOR YOU.
>> WHY DO PEOPLE WANT TO GET RID
OF ME?
>> THEY'RE GUNNING FOR YOU, MAN,
I DON'T KNOW.
>> DO THEY HAVE THE NUMBERS TO
DO THAT?
>> THEY DON'T HAVE ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHO ELSE THEY GOT,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE IT.
>> EVERY SINGLE PERSON THAT
CLAIMED THEY WERE GOING
TO BE STRONG SIX TOTALLY LIED.
AND THERE I AM THE FOOL THAT WAS
SITTING THERE LIKE I REALLY AM
GOING TO DO THIS TO THESE
PEOPLE.
>> BUT YOU HAVE TO BUST YOUR
ASS.
>> I WAS THINKING OF ANOTHER
PLAN, OTHER THAN JUST WINNING.
I'VE GOT TO GET SOME NUMBERS.
>> WHO?
EVERYBODY IS AGAINST YOU.
>> WHY IS EVERYBODY AGAINST ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I BUSTED MY ASS SINCE DAY ONE
OUT HERE.
>> EVERYTHING EVERYBODY IS
LOOKING AT YOU RIGHT NOW
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE AN ALLIANCE.
I THINK THEY THINK THAT YOU'RE A
THREAT
BUT YOU'RE EASY TO GET OUT.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GRABBED
ALL THIS STUFF.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
>> I'M HAVING FUN.
YOU GOTTA HAVE FUN.
>> IT'S SO GOOD.
>> MY REASON FOR TELLING ALINA
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO BE
THE FIRST ONE OUT, THAT'S A VOTE
THAT I'LL HAVE GUARANTEED
WHEN SHE'S A PART OF THE JURY.
SO I HAVE TO BE SMART.
IF I WANT TO KEEP TALKING TO
ALINA,
BECAUSE I WANT HER TO FEEL SAFE
WITH ME.
I WANT HER TO KNOW I HAVE HER
BACK EVEN THOUGH
I KIND OF DON'T BUT I KIND OF DO
AT THE SAME TIME.
IT'S LIKE A TOSS-UP.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHERE THE BIG
WOODEN BOWL WENT?
>> LAST TIME I SAW IT, IT WAS
RIGHT OVER THERE
AND IT'S NOT THERE ANYMORE.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE FRYING PAN?
IS THAT GONE, TOO?
FOR SURE, FOR SURE?
THE BOWL AND THE FRYING PAN?
>> YUP.
>> THAT DIDN'T JUST GET SWEPT
AWAY BY THE TIDE, YOU GUYS.
>> HEY, WHERE'S THE FLOUR?
>> NO WAY!
THEY TOOK THE FLOUR!
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> THAT'S REALLY UNCOOL.
>> NAONKA, DID YOU PUT THE FLOUR
BACK IN THE CHEST?
I SAW HER TAKE IT AND PUT IT IN
HER BAG.
>> AND I PUT IT BACK, AND I SAID
I PUT IT BACK.
>> YOU PUT IT IN YOUR BAG?
>> AND I PUT IT BACK.
I DIDN'T EVEN PUT IT IN MY BAG.
>> WHY DID IT GO IN THE BAG?
>> I WAS GOING TO PUT HALF IN
THERE.
>> YOU UNDERSTAND WHY EVERYBODY
IS WONDERING
WHY YOU PUT IT IN YOUR BACK?
>> I DIDN'T TAKE IT, UNCLE DAN,
I DIDN'T TAKE IT.
FABIO, I DIDN'T TAKE IT.
SASH I DIDN'T TAKE IT.
I'M DONE, FABIO.
I ALREADY SAID WHAT I'M GOING TO
SAID.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY IT HAD TO GO
IN YOUR BAG.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
>> JUST SO YOU KNOW, NOBODY ON
THE TRIBE UNDERSTANDS
WHY IT HAD TO GO IN YOUR BAG.
>> I PUT IT BACK.
>> WE'RE NOT ASKING YOU IF YOU
PUT IT BACK OR NOT!
WE'RE NOT--
WE'RE NOT ASKING YOU
WHETHER YOU PUT IT...
>> IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE!
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT WAS SO HARD TO SIT THERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I WAS FREE OF
GUILT.
OBVIOUSLY, I'M TOTALLY CONNECTED
WITH THE FACT THAT SHE DID THAT.
BECAUSE I KNEW ABOUT IT, AND I
DIDN'T STOP HER
AND I DIDN'T TELL ANYBODY ABOUT
IT.
THE REASON IT WAS SO HARD FOR ME
TO OWN UP TO IT,
EVERYBODY MIGHT BE EQUALLY AS
PISSED OFF AS ME
AS THEY ARE AT NAONKA.
>> ARE YOU PUTTING MY NAME OUT
THERE?
>> NO.
IT NEEDS TO COME OUT.
EVERYTHING NEEDS TO COME OUT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT THIS TRIBE NEEDS RIGHT NOW,
IS THIS COMES OUT.
>> FOR EVERYTHING TO JUST COME
BACK HERE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY EVERYBODY
HAS TO PUT NAMES.
WHAT DO YOU WANT A NAME?
>> THAT'S THE THING, A LOT OF
PEOPLE NOW KNOW IT WAS YOU.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL SAY IT.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO IS
JUST 'FESS UP.
EVERYBODY WILL APPRECIATE IT AND
RESPECT YOU SO MUCH MORE.
>> I TOLD EVERYBODY INDIVIDUALLY
I DID NOT TAKE IT.
>> YOU LIED.
YOU LIED IN "SURVIVOR?"
>> EVERYONE WILL GET THAT.
>> EVERYONE'S LIED IN
"SURVIVOR."
>> I LIED FOR YOU GUYS.
I'M JUST TRYING TO PLAY THE GAME
BUT I DID NOT DO IT
WITH THE INTENTION TO STARVE
EVERYONE.
ALINA AND I TOOK A WALK.
>> ALINA WITH YOU WHEN YOU TOOK
THE BOWL OUT THERE?
>> I DID GRAB THE FLOUR AND MY
PURPOSE WAS TO MEASURE IT OUT
FOR HALF AND HALF BECAUSE WE
WERE USING A WHOLE LOT OF FOOD.
>> WERE YOU DOING THAT TO HALF
THE FLOUR--
LET'S BE STRAIGHT ALL THE WAY
THROUGH-- OR WERE YOU GOING
TO SAVE SOME OF THAT FLOUR LATER
TO USE IT
FOR YOUR ADVANTAGE AND SHARE IT.
>> NO, I WAS TRYING TO PORTION
IT OUT.
>> SHE'S SAYING SHE WAS DOING IT
FOR THE BETTER OF THE TRIBE.
SORRY, I'M NOT BUYING IT.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO BUY IT.
>> I COULD HAVE SAID, "GUYS,
WE'RE USING WAY TOO MUCH FLOUR.
LET'S CHILL."
>> THERE ARE A NUMBER OF WAYS I
COULD HAVE GONE ABOUT IT
BUT I WENT ANOTHER WAY.
YOU GUYS DON'T NEED TO POINT THE
FINGER AT HER.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT WAS HER IDEA.
IT WASN'T.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THAT'S A NICE
THING...
>> I APOLOGIZE.
>> WE'LL TRY TO MAKE IT EASY.
>> STEALING FOOD OF ALL THINGS,
IN "SURVIVOR,"
YOU WOULD THINK THAT HAVING DONE
WHAT SHE DID,
WOULD MEAN YOU'RE DONE, LIKE,
INSTANTLY GONE.
BUT ANYBODY THAT'S ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK
CAN BE VALUABLE TO SOMEBODY
ELSE.
SHE LIED AND SHE STOLE.
HOW EASY IS THAT?
GET RID OF HER.
IT SHOULD BE THAT SIMPLE BUT
THIS GAME IS NEVER SIMPLE.
>> MARTY.
>> WHAT'S FOR BREAKFAST.
>> IT WAS CRAZY NAONKA WOULD
THINK OF SOMETHING AS RIDICULOUS
AS STEALING THE FRYING PAN,
BOWL, AND ALL THE STUFF
TO MIX TORTILLAS, BUT ALINA
CONFESSED TO BEING A PART OF IT.
SHE'S HAD A TARGET FOR THE
LONGEST TIME,
AND ON TOP OF ALL OF THAT, SHE
HAS THIS?
IT SUCKS TO BE ALINA RIGHT NOW.
>> NAONKA DEFINITELY IS NOT ONE
OF THE FAVORITE PEOPLE IN CAMP
AT THE MOMENT BUT THAT WORKS
PERFECTLY INTO MY GAME PLAN AS
HAVING HER AS ONE OF THE FINAL
THREE BECAUSE THAT PRETTY MUCH
GUARANTEES HER THAT SHE'S NOT
GOING TO RECEIVE
ANY MILLION-DOLLAR VOTES.
>> I REASSURED ALL THE GUYS THAT
ALINA NEEDS
TO GO HOME FIRST TONIGHT, AND
JUST KEEP ON DOING
WHAT YOU'RE DOING, AND KIND OF
PRETEND
LIKE YOU'RE SORRY, YOU KNOW.
AND EVERY DAY IT WILL JUST KIND
OF BE A THING OF THE PAST.
AND IF HER-- YOUR NAME GOES ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK,
WE'LL PICK ONE OF THEM.
YOU'RE MY NUMBER ONE GIRL HERE.
>> DITTO.
>> BRENDA!
>> UH-OH!
>> SHE CAUGHT ANOTHER FISH.
>> FISH DANCE.
>> YO, BABY.
YO, BABY.
>> IS THIS THE FOURTH FISH?
>> FIFTH.
SOMEBODY COME HELP ME GET SOME
FRESH WATER.
>> YEAH, I'LL GET RIGHT ON IT.
THE MORE JANE STAYS IN THE GAME,
THE MORE COMPLICATED THE GAME
GETS.
I THINK THEY ALL SEE THE
CONNECTION SHE MADE WITH CHASE.
I BET YOU THAT CAN'T BE UNWOUND,
THE WHOLE CAROLINA THING
AND "MY MOMMA TOLD ME" AND ALL
THAT CRAP HAS NOW INFECTED CHASE
AND IT'S GOING TO CONTINUE TO
SPREAD LIKE CANCEROUS TENTACLES
THROUGH THE TRIBE.
YOU LET SOMEBODY LIKE JANE GET
UNDER THE RADAR,
THE FURTHER IT GOES THE MORE
DANGEROUS IT IS.
I MEAN, HER STORY IS THE SADDEST
STORY EVER ON EARTH,
AND HER CATCHING FISH-- EVERY
TIME SHE CASHES FISH,
THE WHOLE JANE DANCE AND
EVERYTHING, ALL THAT STUFF,
ALL OF A SUDDEN, YOU'RE GOING TO
BE SITTING THERE LIKE HOLY COW.
I THINK IT'S A DONE DEAL.
ANYBODY THAT GOES TO FINAL WITH
HER, YOU'RE COOKED.
>> MARTY HAS THE WRONG
PERCEPTION OF JANE,
BUT MARTY IS SOMEBODY TO WATCH
BECAUSE HE IS TALKING
TO BENRY AND FABIO AND, DAN AND
IF HE WANTS
SOMEBODY OUT SO BADLY,
MAYBE HE ALREADY HAS A REALLY
GOOD STRATEGY TO GET TO THE END.
SO MAYBE IT IS JUST GOOD TO GET
RID OF IT
BEFORE WE ALL START GETTING
WARPED.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
SHALL WE GET
TO TODAY'S CHALLENGE?
>> All: YES. YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
DAN, I'LL TAKE BACK IMMUNITY.
>> NO MORE BABY CORTEZ.
>> Jeff: TRIBAL IMMUNITY
IS NO MORE.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
IS WHAT YOU SEEK.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU WILL EACH HAVE TWO METAL
HANDLES THAT YOU WILL USE
TO KEEP TENSION ON A STEEL BAR.
IF YOU RELEASE THE TENSION EVEN
FOR A MOMENT,
THE STEEL BAR WILL DROP,
YOUR TILE WILL BREAK,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
THE LAST MAN AND THE LAST WOMAN
STANDING WIN IMMUNITY.
TWO PEOPLE WILL BE SAFE FROM
THE VOTE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
MAKE SENSE?
>> All: YUP. YEAH.
>> Jeff: DRAW FOR SPOTS,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR HANDLES,
GET SOME TENSION ON THAT BAR.
IN THREE, TWO, ONE, LIFT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S RELEASE
THEIR TILES.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
AND PURPLE KELLY IS FIRST OUT.
FOLLOWED RIGHT BY DAN.
JUST LIKE THAT, THREE SECONDS
IN, WE LOSE OUR FIRST TWO.
ALINA IS OUT.
AND NOT HAPPY.
REMEMBER, YOU'VE GOT TO GET
TENSION ON THAT BAR.
TOTAL CONCENTRATION.
BRENDA IS OUT.
BENRY'S OUT.
THIS IS ABOUT WANTING IT.
KEEP DIGGING.
SASH IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
NAONKA IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
VERY QUICKLY WE ARE DOWN TO JANE
VERSUS HOLLY FOR THE WOMEN,
MARTY, FABIO, CHASE FOR THE MEN.
HOLLY STRUGGLING.
HOLLY OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
JANE IS THE LAST WOMAN STANDING.
JANE WINS IMMUNITY
FOR THE WOMEN.
(APPLAUSE)
>> GOOD JOB, JANE!
>> Jeff: YOU CAN DROP.
>> YOU SURE?
>> Jeff: I'M SURE.
>> WHAT IF I WANT TO BEAT THEM?
>> Jeff: GO FOR IT.
JANE HAS ALREADY WON IMMUNITY,
DOES NOT WANT TO GIVE UP YET,
TRYING TO PROVE A POINT
IN THIS GAME,
GONNA STAY IN THIS CHALLENGE
EVEN THOUGH SHE ALREADY HAS
A NECKLACE.
>> SHE'S A NORTH CAROLINA GIRL,
JEFF.
>> YOU GOT IT, JANE.
>> PICKING UP 80-POUND DOGS
HELPS.
>> Jeff: MARTY IS OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN
TO FABIO AND CHASE.
OLDEST WOMAN OUT HERE,
ONE OF THE LAST THREE STANDING
AGAINST TWO OF THE YOUNG,
STRONG GUYS.
CHASE DROPS HIS BAR, FABIO WINS
IMMUNITY FOR THE MEN.
JANE WINS IMMUNITY
FOR THE WOMEN.
>> NICE JOB, FABIO.
(APPLAUSE)
>> I'M NOT BREAKING MY TILE!
>> Jeff: JANE, COME ON OVER.
FABIO, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, JANE.
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: JANE WINS IMMUNITY.
JANE IS SAFE
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
FABIO ALSO HAS IMMUNITY.
FABIO ALSO SAFE.
JANE AND FABIO SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
EVERYBODY ELSE FAIR GAME.
SHOULD BE AN INTERESTING
AFTERNOON.
OUR FIRST MERGED TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP. CONGRATS.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> NICE JOB, GUYS.
>> NICE JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> LET ME SEE MY GIRLS
OVER HERE.
>> CONGRATULATIONS!
>> GOOD JOB!
>> HEY, CAN I GET IN?
>> GET IN HERE!
>> ANOTHER ONE.
>> MY WHOLE GOAL TODAY
WAS TO BEAT MARTY.
>> JANE, VERY IMPRESSIVE, JANE.
VERY IMPRESSIVE, JANE.
(APPLAUSE)
>> I'M JUST TRYING JUST TO PROVE
TO MARTY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I MAY BE LITTLE, I MAY BE SMALL,
BUT THERE AIN'T NO WAY IN HELL
ON A INDIVIDUAL CHALLENGE
THAT YOU WILL BEAT ME.
SO... (GRUNTS, LAUGHS)
>> SO WE NEED TO GET, LIKE,
US GIRLS TOGETHER AND SASH,
AND GET MARTY OUT.
AND THAT'S IT.
>> YEAH.
>> IF YOU GUYS TELL ME YOU'RE
VOTING FOR ME NOW,
THEY'LL NEVER SEE IT COMING,
AND YOU CAN BLAME MARTY.
>> I DON'T.
>> I NEEDED TO WIN TODAY.
UM, I KNOW THAT I'M IN
THE HOT SEAT,
BUT I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE
THAT IS.
I KNOW THAT JANE HATES MARTY AND
SHE WANTS TO SEE HIM GONE,
AND JANE HAS A LOT OF NUMBERS ON
HER SIDE,
AND I HAPPEN TO BE
ON HER SIDE, TOO.
SO I'M TRYING TO LAY LOW,
AND HOPE THAT MAYBE THE DRAMA
THAT'S GOING ON
IS NOT GONNA REVOLVE AROUND ME.
>> I'M DOWN TO VOTE WHOEVER:
MARTY OR ALINA OUT.
I'M GONNA VOTER EITHER ONE,
WHICHEVER ONE EVERYONE DECIDES.
IT'S JUST, WE HAVE
TO GET HER OUT SECOND.
>> YEAH, WE WILL.
I THINK SHE'S A BIGGER THREAT.
>> I THINK IN CHALLENGES,
I THINK HE DEMORALIZES
OUR ENTIRE CAMP.
>> HE DOES DEMORALIZE
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
>> PURPLE KELLY.
>> PURPLE KELLY IS FIVE.
>> THAT'S SEVEN RIGHT THERE.
>> THAT'S SEVEN.
>> YOU GUYS NEED TO, WELL, WE
NEED TO TRY TO TALK
TO ALL OF THEM, BECAUSE AS FAR
AS SASH GOES, IT'S ALINA.
>> MAKE SURE.
>> WELL, EVERYBODY WAS DEBATING
ABOUT MARTY AND ALINA,
BUT JANE REALLY, REALLY WANTS
MARTY OUT, LIKE, EVEN IF WE WERE
TO JUST ALL WRITE DOWN ALINA,
SHE WILL BE THE ONE
TO WRITE DOWN MARTY.
>> SEE, IT'S BETWEEN MARTY
OR ALINA.
I'LL JUST GO
WITH THE MAJORITY, MAN.
>> I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
>> UM, I HAVE TO ASK YOU GUYS
A BIG FAVOR.
YOU KNOW, BACK IN THE FORUM,
I PROMISED MARTY THAT
IF WE GO TO NEXT TRIBAL,
AND IF HE'S ON THE OUTS,
THAT I WOULD GIVE HIM THE IDOL.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY HE WOULD
GIVE IT TO ME.
SO ALL I'M ASKING IS TO WAIT
UNTIL THE NEXT ROUND.
IF YOU REALLY WANT MARTY OUT,
IT'S FINE.
BUT JUST DON'T MAKE ME GO BACK
ON MY WORD TONIGHT.
>> THEN WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
NEXT ROUND?
>> NO, IT'S ONLY FOR ONE TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> WELL, WHAT IF HE WINS
IMMUNITY THE NEXT TIME?
>> NO, IT'S ONLY TONIGHT.
'CAUSE I ONLY PROMISED HIM
THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I GAVE HIM MY WORD,
AND I DON'T WANT TO,
I DON'T WANT TO START TO BREAK
PROMISES RIGHT AWAY.
>> WELL, GIVE ME THE IDOL.
I'LL HOLD IT, AND YOU DON'T HAVE
IT NO MORE.
>> BUT I THOUGHT THE PLAN
FROM THE BEGINNING...
>> THERE'S REALLY NO RUSH
TO TAKE OUT MARTY.
>> WELL, WHAT IF HE GETS
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
THE NEXT THREE TIMES?
>> WHAT ABOUT THE IMMUNITY?
WE HAVE EIGHT MORE TIMES TO GO,
YOU KNOW?
>> HOW DO YOU WANT TO DO IT?
>> WELL, FOR THE LONGEST TIME
IT'S BEEN ALINA.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
I MEAN, LIKE I TOLD YOU
ALL THE TIME, JUST DON'T WORRY.
THERE'S NO NEED TO.
>> I AM HIS TARGET.
>> RIGHT, BUT WE'RE
YOUR ALLIANCE.
>> OKAY. THERE ARE A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT WANT MARTY OUT,
BUT IT ALL GOES BACK TO SASH
MAKING SOME AGREEMENT WITH MARTY
WHEN HE GOT HIM TO GIVE THE IDOL
TO HIM WHEN HE WAS ON
THE LA FLOR TRIBE
SO HE COULD "GAIN TRUST."
MARTY'S ALWAYS A THREAT.
MARTY, TO ME,
IS THE BIGGEST THREAT,
SO I'M NOT VOTING FOR ALINA,
I'M NOT.
'CAUSE I DON'T FEEL RIGHT ABOUT
VOTING SOMEBODY OUT
THAT I DON'T THINK SHOULD BE
LEAVING RIGHT NOW.
>> ME?
>> YEAH.
>> BUT THAT'S JUST YOUR GUT.
>> NO, IT'S-IT'S NOT
A BLINDSIDE.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD DAN.
>> WHAT?
>> THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD DAN, I'M
BEING SET UP FOR A BLINDSIDE.
>> ALL THE NUMBERS, EVERYONE
I'VE SPOKEN TO, SAID IT'S ALINA.
>> CHASE IS NOW DEFINITELY,
IN MY BOOK, A MORON,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T GO TELL
SOMEONE
YOU'RE GONNA BLINDSIDE SOMEBODY
IF YOU HAVE AT LEAST FOUR OR
FIVE VOTES BEHIND YOU.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T EVEN BROACH
THE SUBJECT.
>> CHASE WENT UP TO DANNY
AND SAID WE'RE GONNA BLINDSIDE
MARTY TONIGHT.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE HE'S TRYING
TO TURN ON-ON OUR-OUR GUYS.
>> YOU GUYS BLINDSIDE MARTY
TONIGHT?
>> THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD DANNY.
>> CHASE DIDN'T MENTION
ANY OF THAT TO ME, SO...
>> I JUST NEVER HEAR IT FROM
YOU.
I MEAN, I GIVE YOU ANY
INFORMATION I CAN.
I'M NOT A PLAYER IN THIS GAME.
I DON'T HAVE POWER.
I DON'T HAVE NUMBERS.
I DON'T HAVE AN IDOL ANYMORE.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
THAT'S IT. I'M A ZERO THREAT,
SO TO PEOPLE TO EVEN SPEND
AN OUNCE OF ENERGY THINKING
ABOUT VOTING MARTY OFF IS CRAZY.
>> MARTY'S BEEN COMING UP TO ME
CONSTANTLY TODAY,
ALMOST TOO MUCH.
I THINK HE BELIEVES THAT HE'S ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK,
WHICH ONLY BY BEING MORE AND
MORE PARANOID ON HIS PART,
IS HE REALLY PLACING A BIGGER
TARGET ON HIS BACK.
I THINK HIS BEST MOVE WOULD BE
TO LAY LOW,
BUT THAT'S NOT HIS STYLE,
AND HE'S ACTUALLY DIGGING
HIS OWN GRAVE AT THE MOMENT.
>> EVERYONE SAYS THEY'RE VOTING
FOR ALINA,
BUT THERE'S OTHER STUFF
GOING ON
THAT I THINK VOTES WILL BE CAST
AGAINST ME
AND PEOPLE WILL TRY TO GET ME.
>> NO, THEY ARE.
THEY'RE VOTING FOR ALINA.
I'VE HEARD "ALINA."
AND I'M TELLING YOU THAT...
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M HEARING.
BUT CAN I COUNT ON YOU,
SOUTH DAKOTA WORD OF HONOR
THAT YOU'LL VOTE
FOR ALINA TONIGHT?
>> I'M VOTING FOR ALINA.
THAT'S ALL I'VE HEARD.
>> BUT I HAVEN'T HEARD YOU SAY
THE SOUTH DAKOTA WORD OF HONOR.
>> THE SOUTH DAKOTA WORD
OF HONOR, I HEARD "ALINA."
>> THAT YOU'LL VOTE FOR ALINA.
>> BUT WE ARE STILL NOT GONNA
HAVE ENOUGH.
SASH IS NOT GONNA CHANGE HIS.
BRENDA'S NOT GONNA CHANGE HERS.
>> SEE, THOSE ARE THE TWO SPLITS
RIGHT NOW.
>> RIGHT.
>> SEE, I'M VOTING MARTY.
>> THAT MEANS THERE'S YOU, YOU,
KELLY PURPLE...
>> THE TWO RIGHT NOW THAT ARE
SPLIT VOTES IS SASH AND BRENDA.
SASH IS NOT GONNA GO BACK
ON HIS WORD.
>> OKAY, SO EVEN IF WE DON'T GET
SASH, THEN THAT'S FINE.
HOLLY, JANE, ME, CHASE, KELLY
PURPLE, NAONKA.
THAT'S SIX.
IF WE CAN GET ONE MORE.
IF WE COULD GET FABIO.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> SO I'VE BEEN TALKING TO
EVERYBODY, AND IT LOOKS
LIKE WE HAVE SIX PEOPLE TO VOTE
FOR MARTY,
AND WE NEED ONE MORE AND THAT
WILL BE SEVEN.
OBVIOUSLY, EVERYONE WANTS MARTY
GONE, IT'S JUST--
IS IT GOING TO BE ME OR HIM
FIRST?
AND I THINK IT SHOULD BE HIM
FIRST.
>> IT SHOULD BE NAONKA FIRST.
>> WELL, PLEASE DON'T THROW
A RANDOM NAONKA VOTE.
IF YOU WANT TO, VOTE NAONKA, YOU
DON'T HAVE TO BE PART
OF THE 6-6, AND FIVE WILL VOTE
FOR ME,
AND SIX WILL VOTE FOR MARTY.
IF YOU WANT TO BE STRATEGIC
ABOUT IT, IT WILL MAKE SENSE.
>> THIS IS WHY EVERYBODY WANTS
YOU OFF.
YOU'RE DANGEROUS.
>> I PLAY THE GAME SMART.
>> YEAH, BUT EVERY TIME YOU TALK
TO ANYBODY,
IT'S ALWAYS A HIDDEN MOTIVE.
>> HIDDEN MOTIVE?
>> THIS ISN'T SO HIDDEN BUT--
>> I'M GOING HOME TONIGHT OR I'M
GOING TO BUST MY ASS
TO NOT GO HOME TONIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT ME TO DO,
ROLL OVER?
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
NO, I DON'T.
>> I UNDERSTAND EVERYBODY THINKS
I'M DANGEROUS BUT IT'S EITHER
MY ASS IS GOING HOME TONIGHT OR
I'M GOING TO FIGHT FOR IT.
>> I WOULD PISS A LOT OF PEOPLE
OFF BY DOING THAT.
I DON'T KNOW, WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO SAY, TAKE MARTY OUT NOW
WHEN I'VE BEEN FRIENDS FOR MARTY
FOR A WHILE AND I GET ALONG
WITH HIM AND I ENJOY HIM AROUND
CAMP
AND SO DO A LOT OF OTHER PEOPLE.
>> IT SEEMS TO ME WE GET ALONG,
TOO, BUT.
>> I, WELL...
>> Jeff: HOLLY, THIS IS IT NOW.
12 PEOPLE FOR A MILLION BUCKS.
CAN YOU SENSE THE GAME STARTING
TO CHANGE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, PEOPLE WANT TO SAVE
THEMSELVES,
SO THEY'RE GOING TO DO ANYTHING
THAT THEY POSSIBLY CAN
TO GET TO THE END.
AND IF YOU JUST AGREE WITH WHAT
EVERYBODY ELSE SAYS,
THAT'S NOT GOING TO GET YOU TO
THE END.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE A RISK.
>> Jeff: MARTY, DO YOU FEEL AS
THOUGH BIG MOVES
ARE GOING TO START HAPPENING?
>> I ABSOLUTELY DO.
AND I THINK THE WINDOWS OF
OPPORTUNITY FOR BIG MOVES
SOMETIMES SHUT QUICKLY, AND
YOU'VE GOT TO SEIZE
THOSE OPPORTUNITIES BECAUSE THEY
DON'T ALWAYS COME UP.
NOW, I JUST WANT TO CLEAR THE
AIR A LITTLE BIT
FOR THE WHOLE TRIBE AND
EVERYBODY HERE
BECAUSE THERE'S BEEN SOME
MISCONCEPTION.
AND THE MISCONCEPTION WAS BY
MISS JANE
THEY EITHER DIDN'T LIKE MISS
JANE OR THAT
SOMEHOW I DIDN'T BOND WITH HER.
THE FACT IS, WITHIN 30 MINUTES
OF THE GAME STARTING,
JANE BEGAN A SERIES OF BAD
MISTAKES AND BAD DECISIONS--
NAMELY, ALIGNING HERSELF WITH
THREE OF THE WEAKEST PLAYERS
THAT WERE SUBSEQUENTLY
ELIMINATED.
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
I APPROACHED YOU, AND Y'ALL
FLUFFED ME OFF.
>> I DON'T MAKE AN ALLIANCE IN
30 MINUTE.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW IF I'M STRONG
OR NOT, MARTY.
>> YOU LET THE LITTLE OLD LADY
FROM SOUTH CAROLINA
THAT CATCHES THE CATFISH.
IF SHE MAKES IT TO THE FINAL
THREE, IF YOU WATCH "SURVIVOR,"
THIS WOMAN WILL TAKE THE MILLION
DOLLARS.
SHE HAS THE SADDEST STORY OF
HUMAN TRAGIC LOSS,
OF NEEDING THE MONEY
DESPERATELY.
YOU CAN'T WRITE A BETTER STORY.
AND I WILL GO ONE STEP FURTHER,
AND THIS WILL BE THE LAST
COMPLIMENT I MAKE, BY THE WAY,
TO MISS JANE, IF JANE MAKES IT
TO THE FINAL THREE, I WILL CAST
MY VOTE FOR THIS WOMAN.
SHE WOULD DESERVE IT, AND THE
PEOPLE THAT ALLOWED HER
TO GET THERE MADE A STRATEGIC
ERROR.
THEY DON'T DESERVE THE MILLION
BUCKS.
IT'S JUST HONESTY.
IT'S THE GAME.
>> IT'S PERSONAL.
>> THERE'S NO PERSONAL OR
NOTHING.
I DON'T CARE IF PEOPLE ARE BLACK
WHITE, OLD, YOUNG,
EVERYONE'S WON THIS GAME--
GAY, STRAIGHT, WHATEVER.
IF YOU THINK SOMEONE IS GOING TO
TAKE A MILLION BUCKS OUT
OF YOUR POCKET, THAT'S WHAT
YOU'VE GOT TO BE THINKING ABOUT.
>> Jeff: ALINA, ON THE FLIP SIDE
COULD MARTY HAVE HURT HIMSELF
TONIGHT BY BEING SO VOCAL HARSH
ABOUT JANE?
>> I THINK HE'S ILLUSTRATING
PERFECTLY TO THIS TRIBE
WHAT A STRONG STRATEGIC PLAYER
HE IS AND HOW SMART HE IS
ABOUT THIS GAME BECAUSE HE JUST
POSED HIMSELF
AS THE BIGGEST THREAT OUT HERE.
DO YOU KEEP THAT GUY AROUND?
>> Jeff: DAN.
>> WE HAD TWO PEOPLE ON THIS
TRIBE STEAL OUR FOOD.
THEY TOOK THE BOWLS, THE COOKING
OIL, THE FRYING PAN,
THE FLOUR, AND THEY HID IT IN
THE WOODS.
>> Jeff: WHO WAS IT, DAN?
>> NAY AND ALINA TOOK THE FOOD.
>> Jeff: NAONKA AND ALINA, YOU
GUYS TOOK FOOD?
>> ME, IT WAS ME.
SHE WAS JUST WITH ME.
I ROBBED THE TRIBE, BUT I GAVE
IT BACK
BECAUSE I WAS PUSHED INTO A
CORNER.
BUT, I MEAN, I GAVE IT BACK.
NOBODY WAS HURT.
>> YOU WOULDN'T HAVE GIVEN IT
BACK IF WE HADN'T FOUND OUT.
>> JEFF, I GOT PUNISHED FOR...
>> YOU DIDN'T GET PUNISHED.
>> Jeff: HOW DID YOU GET
PUNISHED?
>> NOBODY TALK TO ME.
>> OH!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: ALINA, WHAT'S YOUR
CULPABILITY IN THIS?
>> I WAS PUT IN A REALLY WEIRD
POSITION.
DO I OUT HER FOR DOING SOMETHING
LIKE THAT AND TELLING EVERYBODY,
THAT'S INDICATING MYSELF, TOO.
THAT'S TAKING THE BLAME FOR
BEING PART OF IT,
AND I WAS FINE WITH DOING THAT
BECAUSE I WAS PART OF IT
AND I ADMIT MY GUILT TO IT.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU DO TO GET
THE TARGET OFF YOUR BACK
AFTER BEING INVOLVED IN THIS
FOOD STEALING?
THE THING IS, JEFF, I'M A REALLY
GOOD SWING VOTE.
IF SOMEBODY NEEDS A NUMBER, HEY,
I'M A NUMBER.
IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS, IF YOU WANT
TO BE SMART STRATEGICALLY
IN THIS GAME YOU DON'T PICK
SOMEBODY WHO IS A POWERHOUSE.
YOU PICK SOMEBODY WHO IS A PAWN,
AND I'M A PAWN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELL THERE'S
CERTAINLY BEEN
A LOT SAID TONIGHT.
TIME TO FIND OUT HOW IT'S GOING
TO PLAY OUT.
JANE, FABIO.
YOU BOTH HAVE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
I ASSUME YOU'RE BOTH GOING TO
KEEP IT.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR JANE, YOU
CANNOT VOTE FOR FABIO.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
JANE, YOU'RE UP.
>> I HOPE EVERYBODY IS SMART
TONIGHT.
>> IT'S EITHER ME OR YOU
TONIGHT,
SO LET THE BEST ARGUMENT WIN.
>> YOU A 100% GRADE "A" DIRT
SQUIRREL,
AND IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO
HOME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MARTY.
MARTY.
TWO VOTES MARTY.
ALINA.
ONE VOTE ALINA.
TWO VOTES MARTY, TWO VOTES
ALINA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ALINA, TWO
VOTES MARTY.
ALINA, FOUR VOTES ALINA,
TWO VOTES MARTY.
ALINA, THAT'S FIVE VOTES ALINA,
ALINA, THAT'S SIX VOTES ALINA,
TWO VOTES MARTY.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ALINA.
THAT'S SEVEN.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ALINA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT'S VOTE
WOULD SEEM TO INDICATE
THAT YOU ARE STILL MAKING
DECISIONS AS A GROUP
AND THAT KIND OF THINKING CAN'T
WORK FOREVER.
SOMETHING'S GOT TO GIVE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
>> IT SHOULD REALLY BE YOU AND
ME RUNNING THE SHOW.
>> Jeff: SASH AND BRENDA
STRUGGLE TO HOLD ON TO POWER.
>> PEOPLE NEED TO REMEMBER WHERE
THEIR PLACE IS.
>> Jeff: AND AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL...
>> I CAN SEE THROUGH MARTY.
>> LIKE MARTY SAID.
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS CRAZY.
>> Jeff: NAONKA LETS HER FREAK
FLAG FLY.
NAONKA, I THINK I'M SPEECHLESS.
>> I WAS REALLY HOPING THAT I
WASN'T GONNA GO HOME.
WHY WOULD
THEY KEEP MARTY OVER ME?
ANYBODY WITH ANY SMARTS ABOUT
THIS GAME
WOULD'VE KEPT ME
INSTEAD OF MARTY.
IT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE SENSE.
HE'S SUCH A BIGGER THREAT
THAN I AM.
THESE PEOPLE ARE STUPID
AND I KNOW, EVENTUALLY,
THE FACT THAT THEY KEPT MARTY
IS GONNA BITE THEM
IN THE BUTT
AND THEY'RE GONNA TOTALLY
REGRET IT.
STUPID MOVE.