>> PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR.
>> SO FAR, MATT HAS BEEN THE
ONLY PERSON TO FIND REDEMPTION
AT REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> MATT STAYS ALIVE.
>> HE HAS WON ALL THREE DUELS.
>> GRAB YOUR STUFF
AND AWAIT YOUR NEXT OPPONENT.
>> AT MATT'S OLD TRIBE PHILLIP
IS DRIVING EVERYONE CRAZY.
>> IT'S SERIOUSLY
HURTING MY EYES.
>> SO ROB ACTUALLY CONSIDERED
KEEPING HIM AROUND FOR A WHILE.
>> AS LONG AS PHILLIP IS
AGGRAVATING EVERYBODY SO MUCH,
IT TAKES ALL
OF THE HEAT OFF OF ME.
MAYBE HE NEEDS TO STAY.
>> SINCE THROWING A CHALLENGE
TO GET RID OF RUSSELL --
>> THIS IS MY LAST TIME
PLAYING THIS GAME.
>> THE ZAPATERA LOOKS LIKE THEY
LOST THEIR MOJO
AND WERE BICKERING
AMONG THEMSELVES.
>> DAVID UNDER PRESSURE
IS REALLY STRESSFUL.
>> DON'T EVEN GO THERE
WITH THAT.
I DON'T FREAK OUT.
>> AND EVEN THOUGH SARITA IS
WEARING THIN ON HER TRIBE MATES
THE BIGGER TARGETS
WERE KRISTA AND STEPHANIE.
>> THERE IS NOTHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, KRISTEN
AND STEPHANIE VOTED FOR STEVE
BUT EVERYBODY ELSE VOTED KRISTA.
>> KRISTA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: NOW STEPHANIE HAS TO
SCRAMBLE TO AVOID BEING THE NEXT
PERSON SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
>> MATT?
>> WHO IS IT?
>> IT'S KRISTA.
ARE YOU DRY UNDER THERE?
>> YEAH, FOR SURE.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'M DEFINITELY
COMING UNDER THERE WITH YOU.
I WAS EXCITED, I SAW HIM IN
THE DUAL AND HE HAS SUCH A
POSITIVE ATTITUDE, JUST
REFRESHING, I GUESS YOU COULD
SAY, EVEN WITH, WITHIN THE FIRST
FIVE MINUTES I FEEL HE HAS SO
MUCH MORE SUBSTANCE THAN THE
PEOPLE I HAVE BEEN ON THE TRIBE
FOR THE LAST 14 DAYS.
YOU PRAY A LOT?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I HAVE BEEN -- WHENEVER I CAN.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE
GOD PUT ME HERE.
>> ME, TOO.
I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT I AM GOING TO GIVE YOU
A RUN FOR YOUR MONEY.
>> OH, TRUST ME, I KNOW YOU ARE.
>> KRISTA CAME IN TONIGHT, I WAS
PRETTY EXCITED TO SEE HER AT
FIRST, BUT I QUICKLY REALIZED
THAT SHE IS A FIRECRACKER
AND SHE IS HERE FOR BUSINESS.
>> YOU ARE NOT SNEAKING UNDER
THE RADAR, BLONDIE.
>> NEITHER ARE YOU, BLONDIE.
>> HEY!
>> TOO BAD.
YOU MUST HAVE A LOT
OF FAITH IN PEOPLE.
TRIBAL LAST NIGHT GOT A
LITTLE UGLY BUT IN THE END
KRISTA WAS OUR VOTE,
AND TO MY SURPRISE,
KRISTA AND STEPHANIE
BOTH VOTED FOR ME.
THAT WAS KIND OF
A COLD SLAP OF REALITY.
>> PLAYING A TEAM --
>> IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU PER SE.
IT IS ABOUT KEEPING THE TEAM
WITH THE STRONGEST COMPETITORS.
I KNOW YOU ARE DIGGING DEEP BUT
IT MIGHT NOT BE THERE TO GIVE.
>> I WAS TRYING TO BE DELICATE.
I AM GOING TO, YOU KNOW, NOT BE
TOO CRAZY ABOUT BASHING PEOPLE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GET SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND AND RIGHT NOW
I AM AT THE BOTTOM, AS MUCH AS I
HATE SUCKING IT UP WITH PEOPLE
WHO ARE COMPLETE -- I WILL DO IT
BECAUSE I WANT TO GET
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> I'M SORRY YOU ARE PERSONALLY
OFFENDED THAT I VOTED FOR YOU.
>> IT IS CRAZY.
WHERE I COME FROM, 13 YEARS IN
THE NFL AND IT IS A GUT CHECK I
AM DEFINITELY GOING TO HAVE
TO DIG DEEPER, BUT HER VOTE
AGAINST ME LAST NIGHT,
I CONSIDER IT STUPID.
>> I THINK IT WAS ANOTHER
POOR MOVE YOU HAVE MADE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> IN ALLIANCES.
I DIDN'T ASK FOR YOUR OPINION
AND IF THAT IS YOUR OPINION,
THAT'S FINE.
>> WELL, THANK YOU FOR
EXPLAINING.
>> SHE IS BASICALLY TIGHTENING
THE ROPE AROUND HER NECK.
IF WE HAVE TO GO BACK
TO TRIBAL SHE IS OUT.
>> WE SHOULD HAVE
ANOTHER BEACH DAY.
>> I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT
WITH NATALIE.
I'M REALLY SCARED RIGHT NOW.
>> OW!
>> SORRY.
>> NATALIE AND I KIND OF STARTED
A LITTLE SPA TODAY, WE ARE LIKE
CLIPPING OUR LEG HAIRS
AND LIKE FIXING OUR EYEBROWS.
>> LIKE WHAT ARE WE
DOING RIGHT NOW?
>> ROB'S MAKING A DAY BED.
ANDREA IS PRETENDING TO HELP.
PHILLIP IS ALWAYS
CHECKING ON THE FIRE.
LIKE EVERY 20, 30 MINUTES.
HOWEVER YOU CAN MAKE YOURSELF
SEEM MORE COMFORTABLE, WHY NOT?
I WORKED HARD ALL OF MY LIFE,
I WAS A BASKETBALL PLAYER,
IN PAGEANTS,
IT IS NOT LIKE I AM LAZY,
NATALIE AND I HAVE JUST
BEEN HANGING.
>> YOU WANT TO GIVE ME
A BRAIDY BRAID?
>> YEAH. COME SIT DOWN.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT YOU GUYS DOING?
HAIR?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I NEED A FRENCH BRAID
IN THESE DREADS.
RIGHT DOWN THE SIDE.
AND A PART RIGHT HERE.
>> GIVE ME THE SCISSORS.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THAT
REAL QUICK.
>> YOU ARE NOT COMING NEAR ME.
>> I WILL GET YOU
WHEN YOU'RE SLEEPING.
>> GIRLS, I HAVE A REQUEST.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> WHAT?
>> AND THAT IS EVERY HALF AN
HOUR OR SO, CHECK ON THE FIRE.
>> YOU KNOW, I DO THAT.
>> I KNOW YOU DO.
>> I AM NOT SINGLING YOU OUT.
>> RIGHT.
>> I AM JUST SAYING, YOU KNOW, I
HAVE BEEN OVER THERE LIKE FOUR
OR FIVE TIMES THIS MORNING JUST
DOING IT, SO WHAT I WANT TO TRY
TO DO LIKE EVERY 25 MINUTES,
HALF AN HOUR YOU WORK IT OUT
AMONGST YOURSELF BECAUSE WE HAVE
WET WOOD HERE
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
>> OKAY.
>> I HAVE IT STOKING RIGHT NOW.
>> THANK YOU, PHILLIP.
>> THANKS PHILLY.
>> IF I GO TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
BEFORE ASHLEY AND NATALIE, THERE
IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH THE
GAME, BECAUSE THOSE TWO GIRLS,
THEY ARE ON A BEAUTY PAGEANT.
>> THAT'S THEIR WHOLE WORLD, BUT
IT IS HARD TO COMPETE AND DO
ANYTHING WHEN YOU HAVE TWO GIRLS
WHO WON'T GET OFF THEIR BUTTS
AND WON'T GIVE YOU
REAL CREDIT FOR ANYTHING.
IT REMINDS ME OF WHEN SOMEBODY
WHO DON'T LIKE DOGS HAD A DOG.
YOU HAVE SEEN THAT.
I AM THEIR REDHEADED
STEPCHILD.
THESE TWO GIRLS MUST GO.
THEY HAVE BEEN HERE 14 DAYS
AND FRANKLY,
THE PAGEANT IS OVER.
>> I HAVE A HEADACHE.
>> I HAVE A STOMACHACHE.
>> LOOK AT HER COMFORT.
>> IT IS REALLY EXCITING.
>> AWESOME.
>> GREAT.
>> IT WAS GREAT GETTING MY
LUXURY ITEM, PROVIDED SOME
COMFORT AND JUST SOME STRENGTH
OF WORDS OF WISDOM AND NICE,
STRONG RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE LORD.
>> IT IS SOMETHING YOU CAN'T
FIND ANYWHERE ELSE.
>> WE GIVE THIS DAY TO YOU,
LORD, AND WE KNOW WHATEVER THE
OUTCOME IS THAT IT WILL BRING
HONOR TO YOU, LORD AND WE THANK
YOU SO MUCH FOR LETTING US BE
HERE TOGETHER ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND, LORD, AND HELP US TO
CARRY ON, HONORING YOU.
>> AMEN.
>> KRISTA IS DIFFERENT FROM THE
OTHER COMPETITORS I HAVE FACED,
FOR ONE KEY REASON, IT IS BOTH
OF US HAVE REALLY BEEN
STRUGGLING WITH NOT HAVING A
FAITH COMMUNITY AND OTHER
BELIEVERS TO KIND OF LEAN ON AND
TALK WITH ABOUT OUR BELIEFS
AND HOW WE FEEL.
>> IT CERTAINLY MAKES IT A LOT
MORE DIFFICULT
TO COMPETE WITH HER.
LAST SCOOP'S FOR YOU.
>> OH.
>> I DEFINITELY HAVE A LITTLE
ANXIETY ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY
THAT THIS COULD BE MY LAST DAY.
>> COME ON IN.
>> ANDREA, AND NATALIE,
TAKE A SEAT.
JULIE AND MIKE, PICK A SPOT
AND GET TO THIS.
>> WE ARE NOW BRINGING THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUAL.
>> MATT WILL BE BATTLING AGAINST
KRISTA, VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO IT?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S DUAL YOU
WILL USE A GRAPPLING HOOK
TO GET THREE BAGS.
EACH BAG CONTAINS A BALL, ONCE
YOU HAVE ALL THREE BAGS YOU WILL
USE ONE BALL TO SOLVE
THE TABLE MAZE.
>> FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
STAYS ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
>> LOSER IS OUT.
THEIR QUEST FOR A MILLION
DOLLARS KAPUT.
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
IT IS DO OR DIE TIME.
SURVIVORS READY.
GO.
>> YOU HAVE TO RETRIEVE THREE
BAGS USING THE GRAPPLING HOOK
AND STAY ON THE PLATFORM
WHILE DOING IT.
>> MATT WITH THE FIRST TOSS.
>> CAN HE HOOK THE FIRST BAG?
>> JUST MISSES.
>> KRISTA REALLY TAKING
HER TIME.
>> GREAT FIRST TOSS AND WITH ONE
TOSS KRISTA HAS SECURED
HER FIRST BAG.
>> MATT WITH A NICE TOSS.
MATT HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
GENTLY PULLING IT BACK.
DOESN'T WANT TO LOSE IT.
>> KRISTA READIES
HER SECOND TOSS.
>> ANOTHER GREAT TOSS BY KRISTA.
>> TWO TOSSES, TWO BAGS.
>> MATT NOW PANICKING.
>> MATT WITH A NICE TOSS.
CAN HE SECURE A BAG?
IT LOOKS GOOD.
MATT WITH HIS SECOND BAG.
KRISTA HAS MADE THREE THROWS AND
WITH THREE TOSSES SHE HAS
GRABBED ALL THREE BAGS.
KRISTA NOW UNWRAPPING.
GET ONE BALL AND START WORKING
ON THE TABLE MAZE.
>> MATT HAS ONE BAG LEFT.
>> BIG ADVANTAGE FOR KRISTA.
THIS COULD DO IT
IF HE CAN HOOK IT.
GOT IT.
GOT TO GET IT BACK.
KRISTA HAS HER BALL AND SHE IS
GOING TO START WORKING.
MATT HAS HIS THIRD BAG AND STILL
LOOKING FOR ONE BALL.
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED.
>> MATT, YOU NEED TO GET
THAT BAG ON.
>> MATT HAS HIS BALL AND WORKING
ON THE TABLE MAZE.
IT IS NOT A SIMPLE MAZE.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF PLACES
THAT BALL CAN FALL INTO A HOLE
AND YOU WILL HAVE TO START OVER.
MATT IS GOING TO HAVE
TO PICK IT UP NOW.
HE DROPS IN A HOLE AND HAS
TO START OVER.
KRISTA COMING UP
ON A TOUGH SPOT.
SHE GETS BY IT.
BOTH MATT AND KRISTA
STILL ALIVE.
KRISTA TOOK AN EARLY LEAD AND
HAS HELD IT THROUGHOUT THIS DUAL
BUT MATT IS CATCHING UP FAST.
MATT IS BY ONE OF THE TOUGHER
SPOTS ONLY TO FIND ANOTHER ONE
AND HE GETS BY THAT ONE.
KRISTA WITH ANOTHER VERY
DIFFICULT SPOT TO GET BY.
SHE IS STILL IN IT.
>> WE ARE NECK AND NECK
IN THIS DUAL.
MATT WITH A NICE JOB.
MATT NOW HAS THE LEAD
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
KRISTA CONTINUES TO FIGHT.
MATT HAS A TOUGH SPOT TO
NAVIGATE, CLOSE TO THE FINISH.
KRISTA FALLS IN THE HOLE.
SHE HAS TO START OVER AGAIN.
MATT VERY CLOSE.
GOT TO GET IT IN THAT NETTING.
MATT STAYS ALIVE!
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING, KRISTA?
>> IT IS A REAL REALITY RIGHT
NOW THAT THE GAME IS OVER.
SO IT IS EMOTIONAL.
>> WELL, KRISTA, YOU LASTED A
LONG TIME IN THIS GAME.
YOU ARE OUT OF THE GAME
FOR GOOD.
>> YOU CAN DROP YOUR BUFF
ON THE WAY OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S A TOUGH COOKIE, BUT --
>> WHAT IS THAT, KRISTA.
>> A LUXURY ITEM.
>> MY BIBLE.
>> I DON'T HAVE MINE SO SHE IS
KIND ENOUGH TO LEAVE IT WITH ME.
>> IS THAT SOMETHING THE TWO
OF YOU GUYS SHARED?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, MATT
IS AN EXTREMELY
STRONG BELIEVER AND I THINK, YOU
KNOW, THAT MIGHT BE ONE OF THE
REASONS HE IS DOING
SO WELL OUT THERE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KRISTA.
>> BYE.
>> MATT AND I AGREED AT THE END
OF THE DUAL TODAY IT WOULD BE
GOD'S WILL THAT WAS DONE
AND IT WAS.
IT WAS MY TIME TO GO.
>> KRISTA LEFT HER BIBLE
TO ME AND I CAN'T EXPLAIN HOW
MUCH THAT MEANT TO ME, BECAUSE
THAT BOOK JUST BREATHES LIFE.
I CAN NEVER THANK HER ENOUGH.
>> Jeff: MATT, ONCE AGAIN,
YOU SEIZED THE MOMENT.
FOUR DUELS, FOUR WINS.
YOU CAN HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION
AND AWAIT YOUR NEXT OPPONENT.
>> THANKS.
>> KRISTA GAVE HIM HER LUXURY
ITEM, A BIBLE ON HER WAY OUT,
AND THEY WERE SO CLOSE, AND THEN
MY WHOLE IMAGE OF MATT CHANGED.
I HAD A GOOD VIBE WITH HIM BUT
OBVIOUSLY HE BONDED
WITH KRISTA JUST AS WELL.
SO EVEN THOUGH INITIALLY I WANT
MATT TO STAY IN AS LONG AS
POSSIBLE, HE CAN BE A VERY
DANGEROUS AS WELL.
>> IS YOUR TOOTH BOTHERING YOU?
>> YEAH.
IT'S NOT MY TOOTH.
I CLEANED IT A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
AND I GOT BACTERIA IN IT.
IT WILL GO AWAY.
>> IT HURTS.
>> POOR SARITA, SHE THOUGHT SHE
HAD A CAVITY AND SAID SOME
BACTERIA GOT INTO IT, I DON'T
KNOW HOW SHE KNOWS THAT.
SHE IS KIND OF A DRAMA QUEEN
PRINCESS.
>> SARITA, SHE IS A TWO-FACED
GIRL FOR THIS KIND OF GAME.
SHE CLEANED HER TEETH
WITH A PIECE OF DIRTY STICK
AND GOUGED HER GUM.
THAT'S A GOOD WAY
TO REALLY GET OUT OF
THE GAME ON YOUR OWN.
OUT HERE, EVERYTHING IS NASTY,
AND STICKING STUFF LIKE THAT
IN HER MOUTH.
I MEAN WHO IN GOD'S NAME WOULD
WORRY ABOUT YOUR BACK TEETH.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
SARITA'S WEARING ON ME.
>> SARITA IS GOING NUTS TOO.
>> I MEAN, OH, MY GOD.
>> YES, REALLY IS.
>> YOU HAVE TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO UNSEAT HER IN THE GROUP.
>> BECAUSE QUITE FRANKLY, IF IT
IS ME IN A FIGHT WITH THEM,
I WILL SHOOT MYSELF.
>> STEPHANIE IS A
CAPABLE COMPETITOR IN THE
CHALLENGES AND I THINK
UNQUESTIONABLY
SARITA IS THE WEAKEST PLAYER
IN THE TRIBE.
>> IF THERE IS A WAY TO GET
STEPHANIE TO BE MORE A PART
OF THE GROUP
AND ULTIMATELY KEEP HER
I WOULD DO THAT
TO SACRIFICE SARITA.
SO I THINK YOU, IN THE SENSE
THAT YOU MAY NOT HAVE A LOT OF
TIME, YOU SHOULD TRY AND TALK TO
EVERYONE INDIVIDUALLY TODAY.
>> I MEAN YOU CANNOT
BE PUSHY ABOUT IT.
>> I CAN'T BE PUSHY AT ALL.
>> I'M GONNA GO HAUL
SOME WOOD IN.
> I SEE THE CLOUDS COMING IN,
PROBABLY GOING TO GET AN EARLY
RAIN LIKE WE DID LAST NIGHT.
I CONSIDER THIS THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE BEEN FRUSTRATED
WITH NATALIE AND ASHLEY, THEY
LAY AROUND WHEN THEY SEE THAT
THERE IS WORK TO BE DONE, THAT I
MIGHT BE ABLE TO USE
SOME ASSISTANCE.
>> HE DOESN'T ASK.
HE SAID, "START GATHERING WOOD."
THAT IS NOT ASKING,
THAT IS DICTATING.
>> AND THE GIRLS ARE GETTING THE
FRUITS OF MY LABOR BUT THEY ARE
NOT GIVING ME ONE IOTA
OF CREDIT FOR IT, ZERO.
>> AND I AM NOT GOING TO STAY
THERE AND SAY, GIRLS, CAN'T YOU
SEE HOW HARD I AM WORKING,
GIVE ME SOME LOVE TOO.
I AM NOT GOING TO PLAY
THAT GAME.
>> WHAT CAN THE GIRLS DO?
WHAT DO YOU WANT THEM TO DO?
>> NOTHING.
BUT THEY ARE 19, 20-YEAR-OLD
GIRLS, THEY ARE NOT GOING
TO DO ANYTHING.
>> THEY ARE NOT GOING TO DO
ANYTHING.
>> AND I AM NOT GOING TO BE
THE ONE TO TRY AND TELL THEM.
>> I AM NOT GOING
TO SUGARCOAT IT ANYMORE.
>> IT IS LIKE I ASKED YOU GUYS
FOUR TIMES TO HELP OUT WITH THE
WOOD, YOU HAVE BEEN
LIKE STATUES STANDING HERE.
>> WHY DO YOU TALK TO THE GIRLS
A CERTAIN WAY BUT NOTHING
TO THE GUYS.
>> I DO.
IN FACT I SAID WOULD YOU HELP
GATHER WOOD AND THEY IMMEDIATELY
STARTED DOING IT.
>> AM I WRONG?
>> DID YOU ASK THEM A DIFFERENT
WAY, YOU COME UP TO US AND SAY,
"STORM IS COMING, GATHER WOOD."
>> I AM TIRED OF IT.
>> I TELL YOU WHAT,
TOMORROW I AM FIRE FREE DAY.
>> I WON'T HAVE TO SAY ANYTHING
TO THE BOYS BECAUSE THEY PULL
THEIR WEIGHT.
WE PULL OUR WEIGHT
AND SO DOES ANDREA.
>> SHE MAKES IT RIGHT AND GOES
GET WATER AND DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE TOLD.
YOU LAY HERE LIKE BEAUTY QUEENS.
>> I AM TIRED OF BEING
THE RED STEPCHILD TO YOU TOO.
>> GET OFF YOUR BUTT
AND HELP OUT AROUND HERE.
>> ARE YOU STILL TALKING?
>> YES, I AM.
>> YOU ARE GOING TO SEE A NEW
ATTITUDE OF ME AROUND HERE.
>> A NEW ATTITUDE, PHILLIP,
WE HAVE SEEN IT BEFORE.
>> COOL.
>> GET USE TO IT, BEAUTY QUEENS.
>> THANK YOU.
THAT'S A COMPLIMENT.
>> YOU SEE THE FIRE IS GOING,
WHATEVER AND YOU WON'T DO IT
UNTIL SOMEBODY SAYS SOMETHING.
>> WE ARE GOING TO WALK AWAY.
>> WALK AWAY AND I WILL FOLLOW
YOU IF YOU WANT ME TO.
>> IF YOU WANT ME TO FOLLOW YOU,
I WILL FOLLOW YOU.
>> HE IS LIKE MENTAL,
HE LITERALLY HAS A MENTAL --
SOMEBODY NEEDS TO DIAGNOSE HIM.
>> YOU LAY AROUND THE ENTIRE DAY
IN YOUR R AND R MODE.
>> IT IS JUST ANNOYING.
I AM DONE WITH HIM, DONE.
>> IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
GET TOUGH.
>> I THINK THIS IS GOING TO END
UP SPLITTING THE TRIBE.
>> THE BEST THING FOR US TO DO
IS KEEP WINNING AND NOT GET RID
OF ANYONE, SO IMMEDIATELY I SAID
I NEED TO TAKE PHILLIP ASIDE AND
I NEED TO SQUASH THIS THING
RIGHT AWAY.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU DON'T
WANT TO TAKE IT ANYMORE AND I
FULLY LIKE I HAVE BEEN IN THAT
POSITION AND I GET IT, I JUST
THINK AT THIS POINT THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING
HAS TO BE TEAM UNITY.
>> IT IS LIKE A PEACE PROCESS TO
BRING THE TRIBE BACK
TOGETHER AGAIN.
>> PHILLIP WAS RIGHT, THE GIRLS
WEREN'T DOING ANYTHING BUT THE
LESS THEY DO THE HAPPIER I AM.
I DON'T WANT THEM TO WORK HARD
AND, YOU KNOW, GIVING US A
REASON TO WRITE THEIR NAME DOWN
AND WIN A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> I WANT TO BORE THE HECK OUT
OF EVERYONE AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
>> THAT'S THE WAY I LIKE IT.
>> GUYS.
>> HE IS NOT GOING TO BE
VERY HAPPY.
>> THE FIRST THING
ON MY TO DO LIST
OF TRYING TO GET BACK INTO
THIS TRIBE IS TO TALK TO STEVE,
BUT I HATE APOLOGIZING FOR STUFF
LIKE THAT, SO IT IS LIKE, OKAY.
SUCK IT UP.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> HEY, I AM NOT REALLY GOOD AT
THIS, BUT I WANT TO SAY I'M
SORRY FOR VOTING FOR YOU.
I KNOW I KIND OF HURT YOUR
FEELINGS BUT THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
>> STEPHANIE TOOK A MOMENT AND
REALLY TRIED TO EITHER PLAY THE
GAME A LITTLE BETTER OR TRY TO
WIN ME OVER OR REALLY COMING
FROM HER HEART, I AM NOT SURE.
>> I APPRECIATE YOU SAYING THAT.
THANK YOU.
>> THAT MEANS A LOT TO ME.
>> BRINGING US TOGETHER,
YOU KNOW.
>> I KNOW.
AND IT IS GOOD TO HAVE
A POSITIVE ATTITUDE.
>> I KNOW SHE IS WORKING HARD,
SO I AM GOING TO KEEP THAT DOOR
OPEN WITH STEPHANIE.
I ALWAYS TRY TO BELIEVE IN
PEOPLE UNTIL THEY ABSOLUTELY,
YOU KNOW,
UNTIL I GET STOMPED ON.
>> YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
THE HONEST TRUTH?
>> YEAH.
>> THE NAME I DO WANT
TO WRITE DOWN.
I WANTED TO WRITE DOWN
SARITA'S NAME.
>> I JUST SEE HER AS THE WEAKEST
PERSON IN THE TRIBE,
BUT IT'S JUST THE POSITION
I AM IN--
IT'S LIKE I HAVE TO KEEP THAT
TO MYSELF.
>> I AM THINKING IT TOO.
YOU'RE STRONGER
IN THE CHALLENGES,
YOU'RE STRONGER AROUND CAMP,
YOU'RE STRONGER
ALL THE WAY AROUND.
>> STEVE AGREES WITH ME THAT
SARITA IS A WEAKER COMPETITOR,
SO I WOULD LOVE TO GO INTO A
CHALLENGE WHERE I COULD SHOW OFF
EVERYTHING I HAVE AND THEN
SARITA IS LACKING AND PICK UP
HER SLACK AND WIN THE CHALLENGE
AND EVERYONE IS REALLY HAPPY
WITH ME AND I WOULD FEEL GREAT.
>> ANY SINGLE THING
WOULD HELP ME AT THIS POINT.
I MEAN, NEED TO DRAG HER DOWN
AND BRING ME UP.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
MIKE, WHERE IS THE ANIMOSITY
LEVEL RIGHT NOW BETWEEN
OMETEPE AND ZAPATERA?
>> I THINK THERE IS A LITTLE
CLASH GOING ON RIGHT NOW, JEFF.
YOU KNOW, WE ARE IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS COMPETITION AND BOTH
TRIBES DESPERATELY WANT TO WIN,
SO I THINK IT IS GOING TO BE
A GOOD CHALLENGE TODAY.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP,
ARE YOU FEELING THAT?
THAT THERE REALLY IS A RIVALRY?
>> OH, ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: WHICH ANIMAL
ARE YOU USING TODAY?
>> BOTH.
>> Jeff: BOTH. BOTH?
>> Jeff: STEVE, A LITTLE
CONCERN HE HAS THE GORILLA
AND THE LION?
>> OH, FOREARM.
>> Jeff: YOU CATCH THAT,
PHILLIP?
>> I CAUGHT IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
I AM READY TO GET
TO THIS CHALLENGE.
SHALL WE? ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, I WILL TAKE
BACK THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, TWO
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL BE
RESPONSIBLE FOR LAUNCHING BALLS
OUT ON TO THE BEACH WHERE THE
REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL CATCH THE BALLS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT COLOR A BALL IS.
IF YOU CATCH A BALL, YOU SCORE
A POINT FOR YOUR TRIBE.
FIRST TRIBE TO FIVE
WINS IMMUNITY.
THE LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE ONE PERSON WILL BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND, IN ADDITION
YOU ARE PLAYING FOR AN AWARD,
THE WINNER WILL BE TAKEN TO A
BEAUTIFUL SPOT HIGH ON THE
MOUNTAIN OVERLOOKING THE VIEW
WHERE YOU WILL ENJOY
A NICE PICNIC LUNCH.
SOUND GOOD?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA, YOU HAVE
ONE EXTRA MEMBER, WHO ARE YOU
GOING TO SIT OUT?
SARITA,
DIDN'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
SARITA, TAKE A SPOT
ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE I WILL GIVE YOU
A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
LAUNCHING THE BALLS
FOR ZAPATERA,
STEPHANIE AND DAVID.
FOR OMETEPE, IT IS NATALIE
AND PHILLIP.
OUT ON THE BEACH, THE MATCHUPS,
WE HAVE GRANT AND MIKE.
NFL PLAYER TAKING ON THE MARINE.
BIG MATCHUP.
BOSTON ROB GOING AGAINST STEVE.
DEEP IN THE BACK
WE HAVE JULIE AND ANDREA.
AND ASHLEY AND RALPH.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY.
THREE, TWO, ONE, RELEASE!
NATALIE GOES SPORT AND GREG
CONNECTS SCORING ONE
FOR OMETEPE.
STEPHANIE GOES DEEP.
JULIE IN AND OUT.
NO SCORE FOR ZAPATERA.
>> OMETEPE LEADS ONE-ZIP.
HERE WE GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
IN THE AIR WITH A LINE DRIVE.
OH, ANDREA MAKES A DIVE FOR IT.
NATALIE GOES SHORT.
CHRIS CONNECTS, CHRIS SCORES
ANOTHER POINT FOR OMETEPE.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> NATALIE GRANT CONNECTION
IS WORKING.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> GET IT IN THE NET, GUYS!
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO, THREE,
TWO, ONE! RELEASE.
DAVID IS DEEP TO RALPH.
NO POINT.
MIKE, TRYING TO HOLD GRANT, HE
CAN'T DO IT, NATALIE GOES SHORT
TO GRANT, GRANT CONNECTS AGAIN!
>> YOU HAVE GOT TO CATCH
SOMETHING.
COME ON.
GOOD STRATEGY BETWEEN NATALIE
AND GRANT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IS PRAYING THE STRATEGY?
>> COME ON, GUYS, LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: OMETEPE NOW LEADS
THREE-ZIP.
PLAYING TO 5.
COME ON, GUYS.
HERE WE GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
MIKE RIPPING GRANT'S SHIRT OFF.
NATALIE GOES SHORT FOR GRANT.
IN AND OUT.
STEPHANIE GOES DEEP, RIGHT THERE
WITH ANOTHER POINT FOR OMETEPE.
STEALS ONE FROM ZAPATERA.
>> OMETEPE LEADS 4-ZIP.
GRANT RIPS OFF WHAT IS LEFT OF
HIS SHIRT, PRESENTS IT TO MIKE
WHO BASICALLY HAS BEEN TEARING
IT OFF EVERY POINT.
THIS COULD BE THE FINAL POINT
FOR OMETEPE.
OMETEPE LEADS 4-ZIP.
WE ARE PLAYING TO FIVE.
HERE WE GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
NATALIE GOES SHORT.
NO, IN AND OUT.
STEVE --
>> ROB JUST MISSES
THE WINNING POINT FOR OMETEPE!
>> MIKE AND GRANT HAVE BEEN
GOING AT IT HARD.
MIKE UNABLE TO SCORE BUT DOING
HIS BEST TO SLOW GRANT DOWN.
THAT HAS NOT BEEN
PARTICULARLY SUCCESSFUL.
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
KEEP IT UP, LET'S PUT IT
TO BED RIGHT HERE.
>> OMETEPE LEADS 4-ZIP AND WE
ARE PLAYING TO FIVE.
IMMUNITY AND A BIG REWARD.
THIS COULD BE IT.
HERE WE GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
STEPHANIE GOES DEEP.
BOSTON ROB, IN AND OUT.
NATALIE GOES SHORT.
GRANT WITH THE FIFTH
AND FINAL POINT!
OMETEPE WINS IMMUNITY
AND REWARD!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE,
CONGRATULATIONS AGAIN.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT
FOR OMETEPE.
BIG REWARD, GO SOMEWHERE
DIFFERENT, ENJOY SOME FOOD.
HEAD OUT AND ENJOY
YOUR AFTERNOON.
ALL RIGHT, ZAPATERA, GRAB YOUR
STUFF AND HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
WHERE SOMEONE WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THE GAME AND SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> OUR DECISION TONIGHT IS VITAL
GOING INTO THE NEXT CHALLENGE.
WE HAVE LOST TWO IN A ROW AND I
HAVE GOT TO HAVE A WINNING TEAM
WITH THE RIGHT ATTITUDE
AND A LOT OF FIGHT IN THEM.
NOT A LOT OF LIP SERVICE
BY STEPHANIE
AND NOT A LOT OF
UPTOWN GIRL LIKE SARITA.
IT IS GOING TO BE
A TOUGH DECISION.
OH, GOSH.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME? MAN!
>> IS THIS A LOBSTER TAIL?
>> COOKIES!
>> THIS IS SO MUCH FOOD.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
THIS IS THE BEST REWARD.
WE HAVE GOT FOOD THAT WE COULD
HAVE EATEN FOR DAYS.
IT WAS LIKE FISH, GUACAMOLE LIKE
EVERYTHING WE WANTED TO EAT
WAS ON THE TABLE.
YEAH!
>> ISN'T THIS A GREAT
FREAKING VIEW.
>> THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE STATUE IS?
THAT IS JESUS FOR SURE.
>> JESUS!
WATCHING OVER US TODAY.
>> THIS IS EVERYTHING WE'VE
TALKED ABOUT, YOU GUYS.
>> OH, YES.
>> THERE'S WATERMELON
DOWN HERE, TOO.
>> NO, THAT'S HOT SALSA.
>> OH, EVEN BETTER.
>> WE SHOW UP AT THE REWARD, AND
WE ALL KNOW THAT THERE IS GOING
TO BE A CLUE TO THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, BECAUSE THERE IS
ALWAYS A CLUE SO RIGHT AWAY
I SPOT THE CLUE UNDERNEATH
THE LOBSTER TAILS
IN THE CENTERPIECE OF THE TABLE.
AT THIS POINT
THERE IS NOT ANY REASON
FOR ME TO DO IT, SO I REALIZE IF
I CAN'T GET IT WITHOUT ANYBODY
ELSE SEEING THAT I GOT IT, I AM
GOING TO LET ONE OF THEM GET IT.
SO GRANT STICKS HIS HAND UNDER
AND HE GRABS THE NOTE.
>> LET'S CHECK OUT THE VIEW.
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
>> LET'S LOOK AT IT
TO MAKE SURE IT IS NOT HERE.
SO AS GRANT IS SHOWING ME THE
NOTE, PHILLIP ENDS UP WALKING UP
THE STAIRS
AND SEES THE NOTE TOO.
>> THERE WAS A LITTLE BIT OF
LIKE, GRANT AND I AND WE GOT
BUSTED BY THE PRINCIPAL.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
>> BACK AT CAMP.
>> HUH?
>> I AM IN AN ALLIANCE WITH ROB,
GRANT AND MYSELF, IN FACT, I
CAUGHT THE STEALTH, I AM THE
SPECIALIST, ROB IS THE MENTALIST
AND GRANT IS THE ASSASSIN.
>> REMEMBER, BOYS, STEALTH.
AND YET TODAY, WHEN ROB AND
GRANT FOUND THE CLUE FOR AN IDOL
THEY TRIED TO HIDE IT.
>> WELL, HELL HATH NO FURY LIKE
A LION OR A GORILLA WHEN HE
THINKS HE HAS BEEN PROVOKED.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO MAKE AN
ALLIANCE WITH ME YOU BETTER
ADHERE TO IT BECAUSE I AM
ALL ABOUT INTEGRITY.
I SERVED MY COUNTRY FOR DUTY,
HONOR, COUNTRY, THAT MEANS
SOMETHING TO ME, AND WHEN YOU
TRY TO TRASH ON THAT, ME AND THE
UNITED STATES GOT SOMETHING FOR
YOU WHEN YOU TRY THAT ONE, BABY.
I COULD DWELL ON A PLACE OF
NEGATIVITY RIGHT NOW BASED ON
WHAT I JUST SAW,
I AM NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
I AM GOING TO SMILE AND WHEN THE
TIME COMES, I AM GOING TO KICK A
LITTLE ASS AROUND HERE.
>> AS A RESULT OF THE LOSS TODAY
WE ARE HEADED TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT AND IT IS GOING
TO BE INTERESTING.
I HAVE LOBBIED FOR STEPHANIE
TO STAY AND SARITA TO GO.
SARITA IS MORE LIKE A TEAM MOM
THAN A MEMBER OF THE TEAM.
THAT'S NOT WHO WE NEED.
WE NEED SOMEBODY WHO CAN
ACTUALLY CONTRIBUTE
ON THE FIELD.
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT ONE,
YOU ALL.
>> WE JUST WEREN'T MEANT
TO WIN THAT ONE.
THAT WASN'T HAPPENING.
WE JUST GOT SMOKED.
>> YEAH.
>> IT IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ANYTHING ELSE RIGHT NOW.
THINK ABOUT THAT.
>> WHAT I THINK IS HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW IS THAT DAVID AND
STEPHANIE ARE DOING THEIR
DAMNEDEST TO TRY TO SWAP HER
NAME ON THE DOCKET WITH MY NAME.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE STEPHANIE
LEAVE, BUT I AM NOT REALLY GOING
TO GO CAMPAIGNING BECAUSE I AM
THE MOST LOYAL PERSON THAT MY
TRIBE WILL EVER SEE
AND THEY ALL KNOW THAT.
>> MEANING WE CAN'T
SIT OUT ANY PLAYER.
AND THE TRUTH IS, I KNOW WHO THE
WEAKEST PLAYER IS PHYSICALLY
AND THAT IS SARITA.
>> THE GUYS LIKE YOU
MORE THAN SARITA.
>> IT IS A TRUST THING.
THEY REALLY TRUST HER.
>> BUT IF WE DON'T HAVE NUMBERS
GOING IN THE MERGE --
>> I KNOW.
>> -- YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO BE
WIPED OUT.
>> IT IS NOT A DONE DEAL YET.
WE HAVEN'T TALKED YET --
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
THE BEST I CAN DO IS SHOW HOW
COMMITTED I AM IN THESE
CHALLENGES AND YOU KNOW
WHAT IS IMPORTANT.
IT IS IMPORTANT TO KEEP
OUR NUMBERS.
THEY KNOW THAT I WANT IT JUST AS
BAD AS THEY DO, BECAUSE I DO.
>> i CAN'T BE ANYBODY ELSE
EXCEPT FOR WHO I AM.
>> WELL, YEAH, THAT IS JUST
YOUR PERSONALITY.
>> STRONG WOMAN.
>> THAT MEANS A LOT TO ME.
>> IF THEY DON'T KEEP ME, THEY
ARE GOING TO LOSE EVERY SINGLE
CHALLENGE, BECAUSE THEY ARE NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE
TO CARRY SARITA ANYMORE.
>> THEY ARE NOTICING THAT.
I KNOW DAVE IS ON MY SIDE.
>> I AM SICK OF LOSING.
WHAT DO WE HAVE TO FOCUS ON NOW?
THERE IS ONLY ONE THING.
WINNING.
TRUST COMES LATER.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
>> WE KNOW WHAT OUR OPTIONS ARE.
>> WHO ARE YOU VOTING FOR
TONIGHT?
>> STEPHANIE IS DEFINITELY
STRONGER IN THE CHALLENGES,
SARITA, I HAVE MORE TRUST IN
SO IT GOES EITHER WAY.
>> I THINK THEY ARE BOTH
VERY WEAK.
I GIVE THEM BOTH
A ONE OUT OF TEN.
I JUST DISAGREE.
I MEAN, I'M SORRY.
I JUST FUNDAMENTALLY DISAGREE
LIKE -- ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS WINNING.
LIKE SERIOUSLY ALL I
CARE ABOUT IS WINNING.
AS WE GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, ONE
THING WE HAVE GOT TO WEIGH
IS IF STEPHANIE GOES HOME,
SARITA IS GOING TO BE
IN THE NEXT CHALLENGE.
SARITA JUST
HAS KIND OF BEEN CRUISING.
STEPHANIE HAS MORE FIGHT IN HER.
IF STEPHANIE CAN PROVE
THAT WE CAN TRUST HER,
I AM NOT TOTALLY OPPOSED
TO KEEPING HER AROUND.
IT IS ABSOLUTELY NOT SET
IN STONE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: DAVID, TAKE ME BACK
TO THE FIRST CHALLENGE
THAT YOU THREW.
VOLUNTARILY LOST
TO GET RID OF RUSSELL.
HOW BIG OF A REGRET IS STARTING
TO SETTLE IN NOW?
>> OBVIOUSLY, WE ARE PAYING THE
PRICE NOW FOR HAVING GIVEN THEM
A BREATH OF FRESH AIR IN TERMS
OF MOVING FORWARD IN THE GAME.
HAD WE KEPT OUR FOOT ON THE
THROTTLE THINGS MAY BE TOTALLY
DIFFERENT IN TERMS OF MOMENTUM.
>> Jeff: RALPH, LET'S TALK
ABOUT TODAY'S CHALLENGE, BECAUSE
YOU GUYS JUST GOT DESTROYED
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> I THINK WE STARTED
THE GAME OUT WRONG TODAY.
WE HAD NO BALLS COMING OUR WAY.
IF I HAD BEEN SHOOTING I BELIEVE
I COULD HAVE DONE
A LITTLE BETTER.
>> SARITA, WHY SIT YOU OUT?
>> I WOULD LIKED TO HAVE BEEN
OUT IN THE FIELD CATCHING.
>> I THOUGHT SHE WAS SHAKING IN
HER BOOTS WHEN SHE FOUND OUT WE
WERE GOING TO DO A CONTACT
SPORT, BUT I AM FINE WITH HER
SITTING OUT
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
SHE IS THAT GREAT
DURING CHALLENGES.
>> Jeff: WHEN YOU SAY YOU
THOUGHT SHE WAS QUAKING IN HER
BOOTS ABOUT DOING SOMETHING
PHYSICAL --
>> SHE WAS WORRIED SHE WAS GOING
TO HAVE TO GET IN THERE
AND PHYSICAL
AND I WAS JUST LIKE,
I DON'T CARE, LET'S DO THIS.
LET'S GO, YOU KNOW?
>> BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO BE THE
ONE THAT SAID OKAY I CAN
DEFINITELY DO IT AND END UP NOT
BEING ABLE TO FOLLOW THROUGH.
>> Jeff: SO THEN YOU ARE
SAYING YOU WERE GLAD TO SIT OUT
BECAUSE THEN YOU COULDN'T
BE A GOAT?
>> WELL, NO.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT SHE SAID.
>> I AM HEARING THE SAME THING
YOU ARE HEARING.
THAT SHE WASN'T GOING TO PUT A
FIGHT ABOUT PARTICIPATING IN THE
CHALLENGE BECAUSE SHE KNEW
SHE WAS THE WORST,
AS A RESULT OF THAT
SHE IS NOT GOING TO BE IN
TROUBLE NOW BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T
HAVE ANY PART IN THE CHALLENGE
AND THE FAILURE.
>> BUT I AM NOT SAYING
I AM NOT GOOD.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN FINE
TO BE OUT THERE.
>> BULL ...
>> I AM A BIG ACTIVE MEMBER
OF THIS TRIBE
AND IT IS HORRIBLE
TO WATCH THAT LOSS.
I MEAN, I WAS REALLY UPSET ABOUT
THE CHALLENGE AS WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT IS SAD TO LOSE SOMEONE,
BOTTOM LINE.
>> Jeff: DO YOU BUY THAT,
STEPHANIE?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I HAVEN'T HEARD ANYONE COMPLAIN
AS MUCH AS SHE DOES.
SO FOR ME, MY IMPRESSION IS,
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE HERE.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA --
>> I AM NEAR YOU
WHEN YOU LIVE --
>> IF THAT'S YOUR OPINION
YOU ARE FINE IF YOU THINK THAT
BUT YOU ARE WAY OFF BASE.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> WELL, THAT'S FINE
BUT YOU ARE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: STEVE, IS THERE ANY
PART OF YOU THAT WONDERS, MAYBE
STEPHANIE'S SPUNK ALONE IS WORTH
KEEPING HER AROUND?
>> ON THE PRO SIDE
FOR STEPHANIE,
SHE IS A WARRIOR AT HEART.
SHE WORKS HARD
AROUND THE CAMPSITE.
SARITA, ON THE POSITIVE SIDE,
IS A TRUSTWORTHY CONFIDANT.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE HER DO
MORE AROUND THE CAMPSITE
AND SEE HER PICK UP
THE CHALLENGE AS WELL.
YOU KNOW, SHE IS A BIT OF AN
UPTOWN GIRL THAT I DON'T THINK
HAS GOTTEN HER FOOTING OUT HERE
IN THE WILDERNESS YET.
>> Jeff: SOUNDS LIKE TWO OF
THE POSITIVES ARE ACTUALLY
NEGATIVES THERE BUT THAT COULD
HAVE BEEN JUST MY PERCEPTION.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH, JEFF,
THE TRIBE IS TOO OBSESSED WITH
TRUSTING ONE ANOTHER AT A TIME
WHEN TRUST IS NOT THE MOST
IMPORTANT ISSUE.
THE STAGE WE ARE AT RIGHT NOW
FOCUSES ON PUTTING THE BEST SIX
OUT IN THE FIELD TO DO WHAT WE
NEED TO DO TO WIN, TRUST WILL
COME WITH TIME, RIGHT NOW WE
NEED TO FOCUS ON WINNING.
>> Jeff: RALPH WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF THAT STRATEGIC LAYOUT?
>> SOUNDS PRETTY GOOD.
SOUNDS REAL GOOD.
>> Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT'S
VOTE IS CLEARLY A BIG VOTE.
WHICH DIRECTION
IS THIS TRIBE GOING TO GO?
LET'S FIND OUT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
RALPH, YOU ARE UP.
>> MAYBE IF YOU SPENT
MORE TIME THINKING
ABOUT YOUR ACTIONS AND HOW YOU
FIT IN WITH YOUR TRIBE,
YOU WOULD STILL BE AROUND.
>> I WILL SEE YOU
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I WILL KICK YOUR ASS THEN.
>> I MADE THE BEST ARGUMENTS
FOR YOU, STEPHANIE,
HOPEFULLY THIS WORKS.
>> Jeff: I WILL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL,
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SARITA.
STEPHANIE, ONE VOTE,
ONE VOTE SARITA.
>> SARITA, TWO VOTES SARITA.
STEPHANIE, THAT'S TWO VOTES
STEPHANIE, TWO VOTES FOR SARITA.
STEPHANIE, THREE VOTES
STEPHANIE, TWO VOTES SARITA.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
SURVIVOR REDEMPTION ISLAND,
STEPHANIE.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT IS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
STEPHANIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
BUT YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE
TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU MADE THE
DECISION TO GO WITH SOMEBODY
YOU THINK YOU CAN TRUST
VERSUS KEEPING SOMEBODY
THAT MIGHT HAVE DONE
BETTER AT CHALLENGES.
WE WILL KNOW SOON ENOUGH
IF YOU MADE THE RIGHT CALL.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES
AND HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR.
>> ONE OF THE MOST
DIFFICULT ASPECTS
OF THE GAME OF SURVIVOR
IS MENTAL FATIGUE.
>> I AM LOSING MY MIND.
>> DAVE IS BUGGING ME.
HE'S A LOOSE CANNON.
>> CRAZY, CRAZY, CRAZY.
>> ROB, ROB, ROB, ROB, ROB.
>> IF WE LOSE,
THE TARGET IS ON ME.
>> WOW.
MY STRATEGY OUT HERE IS TO BE
BRUTALLY HONEST
ABOUT ZAPATERA TRIBE.
>> NO WAY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO ALIGN
WITH MY PEOPLE.
>> I DON'T THINK I DO.
>> THEY ARE NOT NICE PEOPLE,
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT.
>> WHEN I WIN, I AM NOT
GOING BACK TO THEM.
THAT IS OBVIOUS.