>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
SARITA DROPS OUT OF THE DUEL.
MATT SEIZED THE MOMENT, AND WILL
RE-ENTER THIS GAME.
AS MATT'S TIME AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND FINALLY CAME TO AN END,
THE TRIBES WERE MERGED.
BUT MATT WAS UNSURE ABOUT
STICKING WITH THE TRIBE THAT
VOTED HIM OUT OR MAKING A BRAND
NEW ALLIANCE.
ROB AND THE FORMER OMETEPE TRIBE
HAD A NARROW ADVANTAGE AT 6-5,
BUT RALPH, FROM THE FORMER
ZAPATERA TRIBE, HAD A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, THAT COULD BE
USED TO EVEN THINGS OUT.
>> WE PLAY THE IDOL AND THEN ALL
WE'VE GOT TO DO IS REEL MATT IN
AND WE'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE THE SITUATION IMPROVED
FOR ROB WHEN HIS
CLOSEST ALLY WON.
MIKE FALLS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
NATALIE WINS FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
AND WHEN HE FINALLY GOT ALL THE
ORIGINAL OMETEPE TRIBE MEMBERS
ON HIS SIDE, HE WAS BACK IN
COMPLETE CONTROL.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SWITCH.
I DON'T WANT TO FLIP.
IF IT'S GOD'S WILL HE'LL TAKE ME
AS FAR AS HE WANTS ME TO GO.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, ROB
WAS THRILLED WHEN
RALPH PLAYED THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL THAT HE SHOULD HAVE KEPT
AND MATT TRUSTED ROB AGAIN AND
PAID THE PRICE, A SECOND
BLINDSIDE.
MATT, ONCE AGAIN,
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
MATT IS NOW HEADING TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND WHERE AT LEAST
ONE OF YOU WILL HAVE TO FACE HIM
IN A DUEL, AND I HAVE A FEELING
FORGIVENESS, NOT GOING TO BE ON
HIS MIND.
>> FIRST AND FOREMOST, I'D LIKE
TO CONGRATULATE MYSELF ON BEING
THE MOST NAIVE PERSON TO EVER
PLAY THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
FOOL ME ONCE, SHAME ON YOU.
FOOL ME TWICE, SHAME ON ME.
SO I AM REAPING THE BENEFITS
OF MY-- MY SHAME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I GOT BLINDSIDED
TWICE BY THE SAME PEOPLE.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE A MORON.
IT'S LIKE IT'S THE BIGGEST
PRACTICAL JOKE IN THE WORLD
THAT'S BEING PLAYED RIGHT NOW.
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
EXACTLY YOUR PLAN IS, BUT I TOLD
YOU I'D STAY HERE AS LONG AS YOU
WANTED ME TO, AND I GUESS--
I GUESS YOU WANTED ME
TO COME BACK
AND SAY, "HERE I AM."
I TRUST YOU.
THIS IS YOUR WILL.
YOU'RE USING MY STUPIDITY
FOR GLORY.
SO THANK YOU, LORD, FOR THIS
OPPORTUNITY AND BLESSED
BE YOUR NAME.
>> A VERY, VERY SMART PLAY
BY THEM LAST NIGHT.
>> DON'T SAY "THEM."
>> WELL, BY ROB.
>> THAT WAS, LIKE,
STRAIGHT MOB STYLE.
>> HE JUST ELIMINATED
THE WILD CARD ALTOGETHER.
>> I THOUGHT LAST NIGHT'S MOVE
BY ROB WAS GENIUS.
THIS WAS, LIKE, A HIT STRAIGHT
OUT OF A MOB MOVIE.
LIKE, THE GUY COMES BACK.
THERE'S LITTLE QUESTION ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT YOU CAN
TRUST HIM,
BUT YOU JUST WELCOME HIM
BACK IN
AND YOU PAT HIM ON THE BACK,
YOU SIT DOWN
AND YOU HAVE DINNER WITH HIM
AND GO OUT ON
THE FISHING BOATS AND KILL HIM.
>> HEY, ROB?
>> YES.
>> AS MUCH AS I HATED IT.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS A BRILLIANT MOVE BY
YOU GUYS LAST NIGHT.
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> WELL PLAYED.
>> YEAH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> MAN, IT'S PART OF THE GAME,
UNFORTUNATELY.
>> YEAH.
POOR KID.
>> COLD-BLOODED, MAN.
FOR THEM TO SEND MATT BACK TO
REDEMPTION WAS JUST
COLD-BLOODED.
I MEAN, DO-- IT'S A GAME, BUT DO
YOU NOT HAVE ANY FEELING AT ALL
FOR A HUMAN BEING?
>> YOU GOT, LIKE, THE LITTLE--
>> SUPERMAN.
>> SUPERMAN!
>> SO, YOU KNOW, WITH PEOPLE
LIKE THAT PLAYING THE GAME,
THERE'S NO BREAKING
THAT BARRIER.
THAT'S HOW WE FEEL RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S NO BREAKING
THEIR LOYAL SHIELD.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> AM I ON THE CHOP BLOCK?
>> CHOP BLOCK?
OH, THE CHOPPING BLOCK?
>> AM I THE ONE THEY'RE GOING
TO SEND HOME?
>> OH, I CAN'T TALK
ABOUT ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
WE DON'T KNOW.
>> HEY, IF YOU WERE IN
THE TOP THREE, I--
I'LL DEFINITELY VOTE
FOR YOU AND NOT BOSTON ROB.
>> YOU CAN TRY, BUT STILL WE
HAVEN'T TALK--
WE HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
KIND OF POINTLESS.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> ALL RIGHTY?
>> IT'S A HARD--
IT'S A HARD GAME.
>> NOW SINCE WE'RE MERGED
WE HAVE NO CONTROL,
I DON'T THINK.
THAT'S VERY AGGRAVATING.
I HAVE NO CLUE WHAT'S GOING ON.
THEY WON'T LET US KNOW NOTHING.
I MEAN, HOW CAN WE PLAY A GAME
WHEN WE DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHERE TO START?
>> FROM HERE ON OUT WE DON'T
DECIDE WHO'S GOING NEXT
UNTIL THE VERY LAST MINUTE.
>> YES.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DO
THE BUDDY SYSTEM.
NOBODY TALKS TO ANYBODY
ON THEIR OWN.
DON'T EVEN ENTERTAIN ANY--
>> NO CONVERSATION ABOUT US,
JUST THE WEATHER AND--
>> WE'RE GUARANTEED TO GO
TO THE FINAL SIX.
>> YA!
>> ALL OF US.
HERE WE GO, OMETEPE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, OMETEPE!
VOTING MATTY OFF LAST NIGHT
ACCOMPLISHED ONE MAIN GOAL
AND THAT WAS BRINGING THE OLD
OMETEPE TRIBE
MUCH CLOSER TOGETHER.
I HAVE A WHOLE VISION THAT I'M
TRYING TO PUT INTO ACTION HERE--
KEEPING US VERSUS THEM
MENTALITY,
THUS, THE SEPARATE SHELTERS,
THE SEPARATE EATING TIMES.
I WANT MY GROUP
TO HATE ZAPATERA.
IT'S US VERSUS THEM,
AND WE'RE BETTER THAN THEM.
AND WE'RE GOING TO BE ARROGANT
ABOUT IT,
AND WE'RE GOING TO SHOW IT.
I'M NOT.
BUT I WANT THEM TO.
BECAUSE I WANT THEIR VOTES
AT THE END OF THE DAY.
>> WHO?
>> ASHLEY DIDN'T TELL YOU
WHAT RALPH SAID TO HER?
>> NO.
>> RALPH PULLED HER ASIDE
AND WAS LIKE,
"I WANT YOU-- LIKE, IF YOU
MAKE IT TO THE TOP THREE,
I'M VOTING FOR YOU."
AND HE WAS LIKE
ARE YOU GOING TO TELL ROB?
AND SHE SAID NO,
HE DOESN'T NEED TO KNOW.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
THANKS FOR TELLING ME.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HONEST.
SO NATALIE JUST CAME AND TOLD ME
THAT RALPH APPROACHED ASHLEY
AND SAID IF SHE MAKES IT
TO THE TOP THREE
HE'S VOTING FOR HER.
HE'S DOING THAT SO ASHLEY MAKES
A CASE TO NOT VOTE OFF RALPH.
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE
HIS ASS OFF ANYWAY.
OKAY. HE'S NOT GOING
TO VOTE FOR ME, RALPH?
HE'S NOT GOING TO VOTE FOR
ASHLEY,
BECAUSE SHE AIN'T GOING
TO BE THERE NOW
AND IT'S YOUR FAULT.
ASHLEY, YOU COULD HAVE
MADE IT TO THE END
BUT YOU DECIDED NOT
TO TELL ME ANYTHING.
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME EVERYTHING.
IT'S MY GAME.
I'M IN CHARGE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
PHILLIP DID YOU HAVE
A COLLISION WITH A HAWK?
>> NO, I DIDN'T HAVE
A COLLISION.
I HAD A MEDITATION
AND THROUGH THE MEDITATION
I ASKED FOR A SIGN
AND OUT OF THIN AIR
APPEARED THIS FEATHER.
>> Jeff: LITERALLY
OUT OF THIN AIR?
>> OUT OF THIN AIR.
>> Jeff: SO ALL THINGS
LOOK GOOD FOR YOU TODAY.
>> IT LOOKS GOOD FOR THE
ALLIANCE OF THE FORMER
OMETEPE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, GOTTA TAKE
BACK THE NECKLACE.
YOU DON'T EVEN WANT TO HELP ME.
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
DIG DOWN TO RETRIEVE A CLUB
AND USE IT TO SMASH A TILE.
THE FIRST SIX MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT ROUND WHERE YOU MUST
SUBMERGE YOUR HEAD
IN A WATER TROUGH,
TAKE IN A MOUTH FULL OF WATER,
THEN CRAWL UNDER THE TROUGH,
SPIT THE WATER INTO A BOWL,
FILLING UP A TUBE.
THE FIRST THREE MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND WHERE YOU MUST SOLVE
A BLOCK PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO GET
THE PUZZLE RIGHT
WINS IMMUNITY AND IS SAFE
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOSER, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
WHERE MATT IS ANXIOUSLY
AWAITING YOUR ARRIVAL.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, WE'LL DRAW
FOR SPOTS AND GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FIRST SIX MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU'VE GOT TO DIG UP THE CLUB,
UNTIE THE KNOTS,
AND THEN SMASH THE TILE.
EVERYBODY DOING A NICE JOB.
GRANT AND ROB ARE THROUGH.
HELLO!
RALPH IS THROUGH.
MIKE IS THROUGH.
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR TWO MORE SPOTS.
DAVID WORKING ON HIS KNOTS.
JULIE WORKING ON THOSE KNOTS.
STEVE WORKING ON HIS KNOTS.
DAVID AND JULIE MOVING ON!
HERE WE GO.
FIRST THREE TO FINISH
MOVE ON TO THE FINAL ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU'VE GOT TO SUBMERGE
YOUR HEAD,
GET WATER, CRAWL UNDER,
AND SPIT IT INTO YOUR BOWL.
GRANT AND ROB DOING
A VERY GOOD JOB.
>> YEAH, GRANT,
YOU'RE DOING IT BABY.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> GREAT JOB, GRANT, KEEP IT UP.
KEEP PUSHING, KEEP PUSHING.
>> Jeff: GRANT VERY FAST
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> KEEP IT UP, BOYS!
>> Jeff: THREE PEOPLE
ARE MOVING ON.
>> KEEP IT UP, GRANT,
KEEP IT UP, GRANT.
YOU'RE KILLING IT BABY,
THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: GRANT VERY CLOSE NOW.
MIKE VERY CLOSE.
ONE MORE GULP COULD DO IT.
>> A BIG ONE, ROB.
COME ON, BABY, YOU GOT IT.
>> KEEP IT UP, ROB.
>> THIS IS IT.
THIS IS IT.
>> Jeff: WILL THIS BE ENOUGH
FOR GRANT?
GRANT MOVING ON!
>> GOOD JOB, GRANT.
COME ON, ROB!
YOU GOT IT, ROB!
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE!
>> MIKE, MOVING ON!
ONE SPOT LEFT.
DIG!
LET'S GO, DIG!
KEEP GOING, ROB, COME ON.
>> Jeff: CAN ROB DO IT
RIGHT HERE?
NO.
DAVID VERY CLOSE.
DAVID MOVING ON TO THE FINAL!
IT IS GRANT, MIKE, AND DAVID
IN THE FINAL ROUND FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
YOU WILL RECOGNIZE THIS PUZZLE
FROM OUR VERY FIRST CHALLENGE.
WE HAD A LARGE VERSION
OF THIS.
SOLID COLORS WILL BE
ON THE INSIDE AND THE BOTTOM.
THE PATTERN WILL BE
ON THE OUTSIDE.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, GRANT.
THERE YOU GO, BABY.
>> GOOD JOB, GRANT.
>> Jeff: TWO FORMER ZAPATERA,
ONE FORMER OMETEPE.
IT IS ONE MERGED TRIBE
BUT AS WE FOUND OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL,
THAT DOES NOT MEAN EVERYBODY
IS GETTING ALONG.
A WIN HERE WOULD BE NICE
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
GRANT DOING A NICE JOB.
IF HE'S RIGHT, HE'S CLOSE.
MIKE RIGHT ON HIS TAIL.
>> COME ON, MIKE.
YOU CAN DO IT, MAN.
>> JUST FOCUS.
YOU GOT IT.
>> COME ON, MIKE, YOU GOT IT.
>> DOING A GOOD JOB, GRANT.
>> Jeff: GRANT THINKS
HE'S GETTING CLOSER.
BIG IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
GRANT AND MIKE BOTH TRYING
TO FIT THEIR LAST PIECE.
>> YEAH, BABY.
>> YEAH, GRANT!
>> WORK IT, GRANT.
>> Jeff: GRANT THINKS HE HAS IT.
>> YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: GRANT WINS IMMUNITY!
>> I'M HORRIBLE AT THOSE THINGS.
>> Jeff: GRANT, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
NICE JOB, MAN.
>> OOOH!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: GRANT SAFE FROM THE
VOTE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
WILL BE SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
WAS SO CLOSE, SO CLOSE.
IT WAS, LIKE, WELL, YOU KNOW,
PREPARE YOURSELF
FOR TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT'S GOING TO BE ONE
OF THE FIVE OF US TONIGHT
UNLESS WE CAN PULL OFF
A MIRACLE, A HAIL MARY.
>> I WAS LOOKING AT YOU.
( LAUGHTER )
>> LET'S GO JUST JUMP IN
AND CRASH THEIR PARTY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
>> WHY HAS THE FLAGPOLE MOVED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT COULD BE A HIDDEN IDOL.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK WE'RE ALL
PREPARING TO POTENTIALLY GO
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WE TOSSED AROUND THE IDEA
OF TRYING TO SEE IF WE CAN WOO
SOME OF THE OMETEPE TRIBE,
BUT ROB'S GOT THEM
ON SUCH LOCKDOWN.
I MEAN, HE'S LIKE THE--
HE'S LIKE THE PRISON GUARD.
>> THEY'RE DIGGING AT THE FLAG.
LET'S GO DIG.
COME ON.
>> WHAT?
>> COME ON, COME ON!
>> OH, THEY'RE COVERING IT
BACK UP!
>> THEY'RE COMING BACK.
>> LET'S SCREW WITH THEM.
>> WHAT ARE WE DIGGING?
I THINK WE INTERRUPTED
SOMETHING.
>> WE WERE JUST LOOKING
FOR ROCKS.
>> ROCKS?
>> I FOUND A COUPLE.
>> THERE ARE ROCKS OVER THERE.
ALL YOU CAN EAT ROCKS.
>> WE'LL STAND BACK AND WATCH.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GO
UNTIL WE HIT WATER.
MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET IT.
>> YUP.
>> IMMEDIATELY UPON RETURNING
FROM THE CHALLENGE, MIKE AND I
DECIDED TO LOOK UNDER THE FLAG.
WE HAD A THOUGHT THAT MAYBE
AN IDOL HAD BEEN PLACED THERE.
BUT THE MURLONIO CRIME SYNDICATE
DECIDE TO GET SHOVELS OUT
AND DUG A FEW FEET DEEP
AROUND THE AREA.
BY THAT POINT IN TIME WE HAD
PRETTY MUCH COME
TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT THERE WAS NOTHING THERE.
>> ANYTHING?
>> NO.
>> NOT YET.
>> I THOUGHT THERE WAS AN IDOL
UNDER THE FLAG, THOUGH.
>> REALLY?
>> THE ZAPATERA TRIBE
COULD REALLY USE IT.
>> THEY CAME RUNNING BACK,
GRABBED SHOVELS.
THEY THOUGHT WE WERE LOOKING
FOR AN IDOL,
AND I THINK ROB THINKS
TO SOME DEGREE
THAT WE MAY HAVE
FOUND IT BEFORE--
BEFORE THEY WERE ABLE TO GET
BACK WITH THE SHOVELS.
WELL, WE TRIED.
>> HERE'S THE THING--
I STILL CAN'T SHAKE
THIS IDOL PARANOIA.
LIKE, IDOLS ARE WHAT KILLED ME
LAST TIME AROUND, AND I'M STILL
STRUGGLING WITH THEM.
I KNOW I HAVE ONE IDOL.
BUT LAST NIGHT AT TRIBAL,
RALPH PLAYED HIS IDOL.
SO I BELIEVE ANOTHER IDOL
COULD BE IN PLAY AT THIS POINT.
>> THEY'RE FREAKING OUT NOW
BECAUSE THEY THINK
WE MIGHT HAVE FOUND IT
UNDER THE FLAGPOLE.
ISN'T IF FUN PLAYING
WITH THESE CLOWNS
OVER HERE ON THIS OTHER TRIBE?
>> TONIGHT, WE BASICALLY HAVE TO
MAKE UP A VOTE THAT COULD
POTENTIALLY COST ME MY
"SURVIVOR" LIFE.
LET'S GO AROUND.
WHO DOES EVERYBODY THINK?
>> I WOULD GO WITH RALPH.
>> BUT WHO IS OUR BIGGEST THREAT
AT THIS POINT?
>> IT'S EITHER MIKE--
I WOULD EITHER DO MIKE OR DAVID.
>> DAVID IS STRATEGICALLY SMART
BUT WE ALSO HAVE TO THINK ABOUT
WHO IS GOING TO HAVE THE BEST
CHANCE TO BEAT MATTY
AT REDEMPTION.
>> MIKE.
>> NO.
DAVID.
>> SO WE HAVE TO PICK SOMEONE TO
VOTE OUT TONIGHT KNOWING THE
POSSIBILITY THAT PERSON MAY
ACTUALLY HAVE AN IDOL OR
SOMEBODY ELSE MAY HAVE ONE AND
GIVE IT TO THAT PERSON.
THIS IS ONE OF THOSE TIMES IN
"SURVIVOR" WHERE YOU
HAVE TO GAMBLE.
HOLD MY HAND.
GET YOUR BUDDY.
>> I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
>> I HAVE TO GO, TOO.
>> WE'LL GO UP HERE.
>> I'VE GOT TO GO, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO, PHILLIP,
YOUR PREDICTION
THAT THE FEATHER
WOULD BRING GOOD LUCK
TO A FORMER OMETEPE MEMBER
CAME TRUE.
GRANT WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE TONIGHT AT THE VOTE.
YOU KNEW THAT.
>> MY GREAT-GREAT-GRAND FATHER,
A FULL-BLOODED CHEROKEE,
CAME TO ME IN A MEDITATION,
AND HE TOLD ME
THAT WAS WHAT WOULD HAPPEN.
HE ALSO STATED
THE FORMER OMETEPE
SHALL LIVE LONG
IN "SURVIVOR" LORE.
>> Jeff: MIKE,
THERE'S SIX OMETEPE.
THERE'S FIVE ZAPATERA.
YOU GUYS ARE IN TROUBLE
RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU COME INTO A
TRIBAL COUNCIL WITH
ZERO OPTIONS,
AND IT'S NOT A FUN SITUATION.
>> Jeff: JULIE, DO YOU LOOK
AT THESE SIX
AND THINK SOMEBODY
IS ON THE BOTTOM?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S OBVIOUS WHO WE THINK IS AT
THE BOTTOM
BUT THEY HAVE NO IDEA.
>> Jeff: SO, THEN, DAVID,
OF THE SIX,
WHO IS ON THE BOTTOM?
>> WE THINK PHILLIP.
>> I ENJOY BEING ON THE BOTTOM.
IF THAT'S WHERE I AM.
IT'S A NICE PLACE TO BE.
YOU CAN LOOK UP AND SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON.
SO, IF SOMEONE SAID TO ME,
"YOU'RE THE GUY THAT'S ALWAYS
GETTING THE WOOD.
YOU'RE THE GUY THAT'S ALWAYS
FETCHING THE WATER."
GUESS WHAT, BEING ONE
OF 12 MEMBERS
IN MY FAMILY, IT'S FUNNY.
I DID THAT AS A CHILD.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, I HAVE A NEW
FAMILY RIGHT NOW
HERE ON "SURVIVOR."
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> MATT THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE HIS FAMILY, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO, RALPH,
YOU'RE TRYING TO FIND A WAY IN,
BUT RIGHT NOW THEY'RE JUST
BLOCKING EVERYTHING.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO GIVE UP,
JEFF.
IF I'M STILL HERE
IN THE MORNING,
I'M GOING TO PUSH
LIKE THE DICKENS.
I MIGHT GET A FEATHER TOMORROW.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
>> IT TAKES COURAGE
AND DETERMINATION
AND KNOWING WHEN
TO HOLD YOUR TONGUE
TO GET A FEATHER.
>> OH.
SO YOU CAN HOLD
YOUR TONGUE, RIGHT, HUH?
>> APPARENTLY SO,
I'M STILL HERE.
>> GOD BLESS HIM.
HE MIGHT GO OUT ON THE BEACH
AND A WHOLE BIRD MIGHT FALL DOWN
AND GET A WHOLE BUNCH
OF FEATHERS.
>> Jeff: WOW.
MIKE, WHAT DO YOU MAKE
OF PHILLIP'S FEATHER?
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S
AN INSECURITY THING.
I THINK PHILLIP IS STRUGGLING
TO FIND HIMSELF.
I DON'T THINK HE KNOWS
WHO HE IS.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, I'M JUST A GUY
WHO GOT A COLLEGE DEGREE,
BECAME A SPECIAL AGENT,
WORKING FOR THREE
SEPARATE AGENCIES.
I SERVED IN THE
UNITED STATES ARMY
AND HAD THE SECOND
HIGHEST MEDAL
THEY GIVE DURING PEACE TIME.
>> JUST GIVE IT UP.
>> I DON'T HAVE TO GIVE IT UP.
>> YOU SOUND LIKE A LUNATIC.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SOUND LIKE?
>> AN EDUCATED INDIVIDUAL.
>> A GUY AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE CESSPOOL
STRUGGLING TO GET OUT OF IT.
>> PHILLIP NEVER CEASES
TO AMAZE ME.
>> KEEP BEING AMAZED
WHEN I SEE YOU SAIL AWAY.
>> Jeff: I GOT TO SAY,
I REALLY HAVE NO IDEA
WHO IS GOING HOME TONIGHT.
DO THE FIVE OF YOU ON
THE FORMER ZAPATERA TRIBE
HAVE ANY IDEA WHO IT MIGHT BE?
>> I HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
IT WILL BE ONE
OF THE FIVE OF US.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GRANT HAS
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR GRANT.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MIKE, YOU'RE UP.
>> PHIL, YOU ARE ONE
ODD DUCK, BROTHER.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT
TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES
ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, PHILLIP.
PHILLIP.
THAT'S THREE VOTES PHILLIP.
FOUR VOTES PHILLIP.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES PHILLIP.
MIKE.
TWO VOTES MIKE.
THREE VOTES MIKE.
MIKE.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES MIKE.
FIVE VOTES MIKE,
FIVE VOTES PHILLIP.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,"
MIKE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
MIKE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU'LL HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
WHERE YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE
TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
>> VERY WELL.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT'S PRETTY
CLEAR THAT THE FORMER ZAPATERA
ARE ON THE WRONG SIDE OF THE
NUMBERS WHICH MEANS YOU HAVE TO
KEEP DIGGING, TRYING
TO FIND A WAY IN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED
ONE MORE SURVIVOR WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
>> TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS
PRETTY INTERESTING.
I THINK THE BIGGEST THING I TOOK
AWAY FROM IT IS THAT PHILLIP IS
SLOWLY BECOMING A VERY LOYAL
SOLDIER.
WHICH IS GOOD FOR ME.
( LAUGHTER )
AND EVEN WHEN FACED WITH "YOU'RE
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE PACK"
COMMENT, BY THE OTHER TRIBE, HE
RESPOND THAT, "I LOVE BEING AT
THE BOTTOM.
THAT'S WHERE I'M COMFORTABLE."
I'M VERY HAPPY THAT PHILLIP IS
OBEYING AND DOING AS HE'S TOLD
AND HE'LL BE REWARDED FOR IT.
PHILLIP'S NOT REALLY CRAZY.
HE'S KIND OF PLAYING CRAZY.
BUT HE IS A LITTLE CRAZY.
SO EVEN THIS EARLY, I'M STILL
THINKING ABOUT MY END GAME AND
THE JURY.
SO AS FAR AS PHILLIP AND I GO,
PHILLIP'S AT THE TOP OF MY LIST.
HE'S MY NUMBER ONE.
THAT'S ALL HE NEEDS TO KNOW.
SO NATALIE AND PHILLIP ARE
COMING TO THE FINAL THREE
WITH ME.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> COULD YOU-- COULD YOU AND
ANDREA SHARE?
>> YES, ABSOLUTELY.
THANK YOU.
>> EVERYBODY THINKS PHILLIP IS
NAIVE.
PHILLIP IS IDIOT.
PHILLIP IS A CRAZY GUY.
THIS IS A GAME.
EVERYBODY WANTS TO STAND AT
FINAL WITH A GUY LIKE ME WHO HAS
BEEN POLARIZING, INSULTING, AND
SO KNOWING BOSTON ROB THE WAY I
KNOW HIM, HE'S THINKING, WHO CAN
I HAVE STAND NEXT TO ME AND WHO
DOESN'T LOOK SO PRETTY?
PHIL SHEPPARD.
BUT I'M A SMART GUY.
I'M A COMPLEX PERSON, AND I
GOTTA MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN.
BUT THERE'S A TIME FOR THAT AND
NOW ISN'T THE TIME.
>> TODAY'S THE DAY.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
>> GOOD LUCK WITH GETTING
THE OPPORTUNITY TO TALK.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S ALL I GOTTA DO
IS GO TALK TO THEM.
>> NO.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO ACCOMPLISH
ANYTHING IF YOU TALK TO
ALL OF THEM.
YOU GET ONE SHOT. YOU GET ONE
TRY TO TALK TO THEM.
IF YOU DON'T GET SOME PROGRESS
ON THE FIRST CHANCE, THEN IT'S
OVER.
GOING OVER THERE AND RUINING IT
NOW--
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
GOING TO DO.
>> DON'T DO SOMETHING STUPID.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WE NEED TO GET THIS GAME
ON THE ROAD.
TIME'S TICKING.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE ON TIME.
WE'VE GOT TO MAKE SOME MOVES.
>> YOU KNOW, A TRIBE THAT STICKS
TOGETHER ENDS TOGETHER.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND WHAT THEY WANT TO HAVE
HAPPEN--
>> UNTIL YOU MERGE.
IT'S ABOUT ONE ON ONE.
>> YOU WANNA WIN THE MILLION OR
YOU WANNA LET ROB WIN IT?
>> I'M REALLY NOT CONCERNED.
>> I JUST WANT TO TALK TO YOU,
AND NOBODY WANTS TO TALK.
>> THERE'S NOTHING TO TALK
ABOUT.
>> THERE'S A WHOLE LOT TO TALK
THIS IS A GAME.
>> WE'RE NOT HERE TO TALK ABOUT
THE GAME WITH YOU.
IF YOU WANTED TO TALK ABOUT YOUR
STEERS AND HOW YOU STARTED YOUR
FARM, WE'LL BE HAPPY TO HEAR IT,
FOR A LITTLE BIT-- FOR A LITTLE
BIT.
>> I WANT TO GIVE YOU MY
OPINION.
>> WELL, WE APPRECIATE YOUR
AS MY GRANDMOTHER USED TO
SAY, OPINIONS ARE LIKE,
EVERYBODY HAS ONE.
>> YOU CAN TALK ABOUT LIKE YOUR
HOME AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH BUT AT HOME, WE TALK
ABOUT THAT WHEN WE ARE
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
THIS IS A GAME. WE GOT TO WORRY
ABOUT A GAME.
>> YOU JUST CAME OVER.
I WAS HAVING A PRIVATE
CONVERSATION.
MOST PEOPLE SAY, "EXCUSE ME."
ANYWAY, BACK TO OUR
CONVERSATION.
>> HE'S SO NUTS.
>> WHEN NOBODY IS WILLING TO
PLAY THE GAME IT'S NOT
A LOT OF FUN.
WE'RE JUST SITTING HERE TRYING
TO HANG ON AS LONG AS WE CAN,
AND THERE ARE NO GUARANTEES THAT
I'M NOT ALREADY
THE NEXT ON THE LIST.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> OH!
>> Jeff: THEY LOOK GOOD,
PHILLIP?
>> OH, YEAH, BABY.
>> Jeff: WELL, I'M HAPPY TO
TELL YOU THAT TODAY EVERYBODY
WILL HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO
FEAST ON CHEESEBURGERS.
SHALL WE GET TO IT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
GRANT, TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
>> MY GOODNESS!
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU ARE
GOING TO HANG FROM A BAR FOR AS
LONG AS YOU CAN.
AFTER 20 MINUTES, YOU'LL BE
ALLOWED TO USE YOUR LEGS ONLY.
ONCE YOU DROP FROM THE BAR,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT HANGING WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE AT THE VOTE.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
NOW TO THE CHEESEBURGERS.
YOU'RE GOING TO EACH TAKE A
WHITE ROCK AND A BLACK ROCK.
TAKE ONE OF EACH.
INDIVIDUAL DECISION.
YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP THIS SECRET
UNTIL I ASK YOU.
BLACK ROCK MEANS I WANT TO PLAY.
I WANT A SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WHITE MEANS I'M EATIN'.
EVERYBODY PUT YOUR PALMS OUT
WHERE I CAN SEE THEM.
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
ONLY TWO PEOPLE OPTING TO EAT.
PHILLIP IS GOING TO EAT
CHEESEBURGERS.
STEVE IS GOING TO EAT
EVERYBODY ELSE FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, GO AHEAD AND GET IN
YOUR POSITIONS.
EVERYBODY LOOKING GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
START EATING.
YOU HAVE 26 BURGERS OVER THERE,
AND A HUGE BOWL OF FRIES.
>> I CAN SMELL THEM FROM HERE.
>> Jeff: ROB LOSING HIS HAT.
>> HANG IN THERE GRANT, ROB.
>> Jeff: HOW ARE THOSE
BURGERS?
>> WOW, WOW.
>> Jeff: GOOD STUFF?
>> AMAZING.
>> Jeff: THOSE BURGERS BETTER
BE GOOD.
YOU'RE GIVING UP IMMUNITY AND A
SHOT, POTENTIALLY, AT A MILLION
DOLLARS.
ROB STRUGGLING TO GET
COMFORTABLE.
EIGHT PEOPLE TRYING TO WIN
IMMUNITY.
WE SWITCH TO LEGS ONLY AFTER 20
MINUTES.
ROB CAN'T HANG ON ANY LONGER.
ROB IS FIRST OUT.
ROB WILL TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
NOW HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO SIT
WITHIN INHALING DISTANCE OF
THOSE BURGERS.
>> LOOKING AWESOME, ANDREA.
KEEP IT UP, ASHLEY.
YOU GUYS LOOK GREAT.
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT DAVID,
THOUGH, HIS HEAD IS STARTING TO
TURN BLUE.
>> I'M VERY, VERY GLAD THAT
PHILLIP IS CONCERNED FOR ME.
>> Jeff: NO LOVE LOST BETWEEN
DAVID AND PHILLIP.
>> I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH
PHILLIP.
>> I HAVE LOT OF PROBLEMS WITH
DAVID.
>> Jeff: DO YOU THINK YOU GUYS
WILL BE FRIENDS AFTERWARDS,
DAVID?
>> BEST FRIENDS.
( BURPS )
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'RE
GOING TO MOVE TO LEGS ONLY.
THIS IS GOING TO INCREASE THE
DIFFICULTY QUITE A BIT.
YOU WILL HAVE TO LET GO OF YOUR
ARMS WHEN I COUNT YOU DOWN.
FIVE, FOUR -- LET THEM GO--
THREE, TWO, ONE.
AND WE'RE GOOD.
>> WAY TO GO, RALPH.
HANG IN THERE BIG MAN.
>> AARRGGH!
>> Jeff: JULIE DROPS FROM THE
BAR, CANNOT HANG ON ANY LONGER.
WE ARE DOWN TO SIX.
>> MY LEG'S GOING NUMB.
OH, MAN!
>> Jeff: ONE LITTLE TOUCH AND
YOU'RE OUT.
GRANT STARTING TO SLIP.
GRANT IS OUT.
AND RALPH IS OUT RIGHT BEHIND
HIM.
>> DAVID, DAVID, DAVID YOU'RE
LOCKED IN.
>> Jeff: WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
>> THAT'S OKAY, GIRLS HANG IN
THERE.
>> DAVID IS STARTING TO MAKE
LITTLE ADJUSTMENTS, GUYS.
>> YEAH, IT'S CALLED SCRATCHING
MY ASS
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jeff: DAVID, THE LAST
REMAINING FORMER ZAPATERA MEMBER
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY AGAINST
THE THREE OMETEPE WOMEN.
YOU'VE BEEN UP THERE
45 MINUTES NOW.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT WILL POWER,
DESIRE RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS NOT PLEASANT.
>> KEEP IT UP, ASHLEY.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WAY TO GO, DAVID.
HANG IN THERE, BROTHER.
>> Jeff: I'M SURE THE
CIRCULATION IN THE BOTTOM HALF
OF YOUR LEGS IS LONG GONE.
FIGHT THROUGH THIS PAIN.
WHOEVER WINS THIS CHALLENGE IS
EARNING IT.
THERE IS NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
>> NATALIE, HANG IN THERE.
>> DAVID, DAVID, NATALIE'S
HURTING, BROTHER.
>> KEEP HANGING, GIRL.
YOU HAVE TWO LEGS ON IT.
HE ONLY HAS ONE LEG.
THAT LEG IS GOING TO BE
DECAPITATED.
>> KEEP IT UP, GIRLS.
KEEP IT UP.
>> HANG IN THERE, DAVID.
BE STRONG.
>> YES!
( CHEERS )
>> Jeff: DAVID CANNOT HANG ON
ANY LONGER.
DAVID IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
>> DAMN.
>> GIRLS.
I REALLY WANT THIS ONE.
IF THERE'S ANOTHER ONE--
>> WILL YOU LET IT GO, ASH?
>> YEAH.
>> DO IT!
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ASHLEY GOES IN FIRST,
THEN NATALIE, ANDREA WINS
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
>> WAY TO DO IT, GIRLS.
>> TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
>> WAY TO GO, DAVID.
>> THANKS.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, WOBBLE ON
OVER HERE.
( APPLAUSE )
HOW ARE THOSE LEGS FEELING?
>> ACTUALLY, THEY'RE FEEL PRETTY
GOOD.
>> Jeff: NICE JOB, GREAT
EFFORT.
ANDREA SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
EVERYBODY ELSE, AFTER 24 DAYS,
ONE OF YOU WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHERE
YOU'LL MEET MATT AND MIKE.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
NICE JOB.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY WHAT A
GREAT JOB WE ALL DID TODAY.
>> A WIN IS ALWAYS IMPORTANT.
I NEVER WANT TO LOSE.
I ALWAYS LIKE TO HAVE AN EDGE.
I DON'T WANT THE ZAPATERA PEOPLE
TO HAVE IMMUNITY.
I DON'T WANT THEM TO HAVE ANY
KIND OF MOMENTUM.
I DON'T WANT THEM TO FEEL LIKE
THEY HAVE ANY POWER.
SO AS LONG AS SOMEONE FROM OUR
SIDE WINS, I'M GOING TO BE HAPPY
AT THIS POINT.
>> I'M GOING TO LOOK.
HEY, WE GOT ALL KINDS OF FISH!
WE GOT 50 FISH!
>> SHUT UP!
>> I AIN'T KIDDIN'.
ALL KINDS OF THEM!
BRING A BASKET.
>> ARE THEY ALIVE OR ARE THEY
DEAD?
>> THEY'RE ALL DEAD.
>> IF THEY'RE DEAD, YOU CAN'T
EAT THEM.
>> THEY'RE STILL IN GOOD SHAPE.
>> NO.
>> THEY'RE NOT?
>> SEE IT?
IT'S LIKE RIGAMORTISE ALREADY
SET IN.
>> THAT WON'T HURT THEM.
WE'LL EAT 'EM.
>> OKAY.
>> HELL, I CAUGHT THEM ON THE
RIVER BANKS AND TOOK ME
THREE HOURS TO GET HOME BEFORE.
>> ROB IS TRYING TO TELL HIS
PEOPLE THAT FISH ISN'T ANY GOOD.
>> THEY'RE ALL SOFT, STILL.
THEY'RE ALL STILL SOFT.
>> I THINK ROB JUST DOESN'T WANT
HIS PEOPLE TO TAKE ANYTHING FROM
US.
NOW, IF ROB WERE TO CATCH ALL
THAT FISH, THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
A DIFFERENT STORY.
THEY WOULD HAVE BEEN FEASTING
OVER THERE.
>> OH, MAN.
THOSE BIG FISH ARE GOOD.
>> I'LL HAVE A LITTLE PIECE OF
THAT.
>> I'M HUNGRY, BRO.
>> THE FISH IS ALREADY
ROTTED AND DEAD.
>> JUST DON'T LET IT AFFECT YOUR
JUDGMENT.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S JUST GOING TO TAKE A DAY
TO GET THESE HUNGER PANGS AWAY.
>> HERE'S THE THING I'M RUNNING
MY TRIBE LIKE THE ARMY.
I'M THE GENERAL, THEY'RE
SOLDIERS AND THEY'RE ALL DOING
AS THEY'RE TOLD WHICH IS A
WONDERFUL THING.
>> GRANT, COME TASTE THIS.
IT'S AWESOME.
>> HOW IS IT?
>> COME TAKE JUST A TASTE.
>> AMAZING.
>> THERE'S NO FOOD OUT HERE, SO
I'LL EAT ANYTHING, NO MATTER
WHAT ROB SAYS.
>> THIS IS A GOOD ONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE NAME OF
THIS ONE IS.
I'M MY OWN MAN, I MAKE MY OWN
DECISIONS.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S A
DICTATORSHIP GOING ON.
>> GRANT, WE HAVE SO MUCH FISH.
REALLY.
>> HE'S BEEN INSTRUCTED NOT TO.
>> HE CONTROLS THEIR DIET.
IT'S AMAZING.
>> THE OMETEPE TRIBE WAS TOLD
NOT TO EAT THE FISH.
I DON'T KNOW IF ROB WANTS TO
KEEP THEM WEAK OR HE JUST WANTS
TO MAINTAIN CONTROL OVER THEM.
IT'S CULT-LIKE.
HE SHOWED THE POWER THAT HE HAS
BY JUST INSTILLING FEAR IN
EVERYONE WITH THE WHOLE MATT
SITUATION.
IF YOU GIVE ANY INCLINATION
YOU'RE WAIVERING IN YOUR
LOYALTY, HE'LL CUT YOUR HEAD OFF
THEN AND THERE.
SO NOBODY IS GOING TO CROSS HIM.
>> I'VE JUST GOT TO SLEEP FOR A
COUPLE OF HOURS.
I'M LIVING ON A CUP OF RICE, AND
IT'S GETTING REALLY OLD.
>> YOU KNOW, WHAT IT COMES DOWN
TO TONIGHT IS DAVID OR STEVE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO LAST MUCH
LONGER, TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
>> DO I ELIMINATE WHAT I
CONSIDER THE BIGGEST STRATEGICAL
THREAT IN THE GAME RIGHT NOW, OR
DO I GIVE THE OLD DYING T-REX
WHAT HE WANTS?
BECAUSE I THINK HE WANTS TO GO
HOME AND GET RID OF STEVE, IT
MAY GIVE ME A JURY VOTE.
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN KNOWN TO HAVE
A MERCY KILLING IN ME FROM TIME
TO TIME.
HAVEN'T I?
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, SAME
FEATHER?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: HAVE YOU HAD ANY
OTHER MEDITATIONS?
>> WELL, THAT'S PART OF IT.
BUT THERE'S ALSO, FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN 22 SEASONS, A HIGHLY
EFFECTIVE AND BEAUTEOUS
AND GLORIOUS OPERATION IN EFFECT
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: WHICH IS WHAT?
>> IT'S CALLED STEALTH.
>> Jeff: STEALTH R US.
>> AND I AM KNOWN AS THE
SPECIALIST.
MY PRINCIPAL RESPONSIBILITIES:
INFILTRATE AND SUPPLANT
INCEPTIONS INTO THE FORMER
ZAPATERA TRIBE.
WE HAVE HERE, BOSTON ROB, THE
MINERALIST.
PRINCIPAL RESPONSIBILITIES --
TO DEVELOP STRATEGIES FOR
CHALLENGING AND DEVELOP
STRATEGIC ALLIANCES THAT ARE
IMPERVIOUS.
WHERE'S GRANT?
THE DESTROYER OF ASPIRATIONS.
BETTER THAN KNOWN AS THE
ASSASSIN.
PRINCIPAL RESPONSIBILITIES--
TO GO OUT AND COMPETE DESTROYING
ANY COMPETITOR.
AND I FORGOT TO MENTION THE
THREE DEGREES WHO ARE HIGHLY
EFFECTIVE, FORMIDABLE, AGILE,
AND HAVE SUPREME ABILITIES TO
FOCUS THEIR MIND LIKE THEY DID
TODAY.
>> Jeff: WOW.
RALPH, PRETTY TOUGH TO BEAT
STEALTH R US.
>> IT IS.
YOU RECKON HIS GRANDFATHER TOLD
HIM TO SIT ON THE BENCH AND EAT
HAMBURGERS TODAY?
>> Jeff: I GUESS THE ARGUMENT
WOULD BE DOES "STEALTH R US"
CARE?
>> I THINK IT'S PRETTY CLEAR MY
TRIBEMATES KNOW WHAT I BRING TO
THE TABLE.
AND, YES, IT WAS DIFFICULT FOR
THEM TO SEE ME DO THAT BUT THEY
KNOW WHERE MY HEART IS.
TODAY I ATE AND I MAKE NO
APOLOGIES FOR THAT.
>> Jeff: STEVE, HOW ABOUT
YOU?
WHAT WAS THE RATIONALE SITTING
OUT TODAY?
THIS IS A TIME WHEN YOU NEED
IMMUNITY MORE THAN EVER.
>> IT'S JUST NOT MY THING.
I'D LAST A SHORT TIME.
SO I JUST MADE THE DECISION TO
TAKE THE
FOOD AND HOPE FOR THE BEST.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, DO YOU SEE
ANY OF THE ZAPATERAS TRYING TO
FIND A CRACK IN THE STEALTH R US
ORGANIZATION?
>> THEY ARE DOING WHAT THEY CAN
TO TRY TO MAKE THAT HAPPEN BUT
OUR ALLIANCE IS SO STRONG, WE
HAVE A BUDDY SYSTEM, AND IT'S
HIGHLY EFFECTIVE.
>> Jeff: A BUDDY SYSTEM.
>> THEY ARE NEVER ALONE, EVER.
THEY'RE ALWAYS WITH SOMEBODY
ELSE.
ROB HAS COMPLETE CONTROL OVER
THEM.
IT'S NOT EVEN A TRIBE.
IT'S A CULT.
>> Jeff: DAVID, AT THIS POINT,
EVERYBODY ON ZAPATERA'S GOT TO
BE THINKING ONE THING-- AS LONG
AS IT ISN'T ME TONIGHT.
CORRECT?
>> THERE'S THAT, DEFINITELY, BUT
AT THE SAME TIME, WITH THE
NUMBERS THE WAY THEY ARE HERE,
IT'S VIRTUALLY IRSURMOUNTABLE,
SO THE OTHER PHASE OF THE GAME,
REDEMPTION ISLAND, MAY BE A
BETTER TACTIC TO TRY TO ADVANCE
YOURSELF THAT WAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ANDREA HAS
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR ANDREA.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ANDREA, YOU'RE UP.
>> HOPEFULLY THIS WORKS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTE ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ROB.
ROB.
IT SAYS, "PLEASE COUNT THIS AS
FOUR ROBS."
IT WILL ONLY COUNT AS ONE.
>> I COULDN'T HELP BUT TRY.
>> Jeff: THAT'S FOUR VOTES
ROB.
DAVID.
THAT'S THREE VOTES DAVID.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES DAVID.
FOUR VOTES ROB.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT THE
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,"
DAVID.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DAVID, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU'LL NOW HEAD TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
>> ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: GOOD LUCK.
WELL, IF YOU'RE A FORMER
ZAPATERA, IT'S PRETTY CLEAR--
YOU HAVE TO CONTINUE TO TRY TO
FIND A WAY TO CRACK THE STEALTH
"R" US ORGANIZATION.
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
PHILLIP TAKES ISSUE
WITH STEVE.
>> YOU DON'T START NOTHING THERE
WON'T BE NONE.
BUT IF YOU START IT, I'M GOING
TO FINISH IT.
YOU NOW CALLED ME CRAZY.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN SOME
WHITE FOLKS THEY LIKE TO TAKE A
BLACK MAN AND MAKE THEM CRAZY
WHEN HE MAKES AN ARGUMENT THAT
YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I GOT TO SAY
ABOUT THAT?
YOU ARE CRAZY.
>> THE LAST FEW DAYS HAVE BEEN
REALLY FRUSTRATING.
IT SEEMS LIKE EVERY TIME THE
WHEELS START TO SPIN AND I START
TO BE ABLE TO PLAY THE GAME,
THAT THE BRAKES GET PUT ON IT BY
SOMEBODY ELSE.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> DAVID MURPHY.
>> WHAT!
>> YEAH.
WHAT IS "SURVIVOR" DOING TO US?
I DON'T KNOW MAN.