>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> OMETEPE SHALL LIVE LONG
IN "SURVIVOR" LORE,
AS LONG AS WE STICK TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: SINCE THE MERGE,
THE FORMER OMETEPE TRIBE
HAS BEEN UNSTOPPABLE.
>> WE'RE GUARANTEED TO GO
TO THE FINAL SIX.
>> WE HAVE THE NUMBERS,
SO IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE
TO TAKE OUT
THE ZAPATERA PEOPLE
ONE BY ONE BY ONE.
>> Jeff: THEY'VE WON
CHALLENGE AFTER CHALLENGE.
GRANT WINS IMMUNITY!
ANDREA WINS.
ROB WINS IMMUNITY!
AND WHITTLED THE FORMER
ZAPATERA TRIBE DOWN TO TWO.
>> HO, HO, HO.
>> Jeff: THE ONLY CRACK
IN THEIR ALLIANCE APPEARED
WHEN PHILLIP'S ANTICS
GOT TO BE TOO MUCH.
>> EVERY TIME I MAKE AN ARGUMENT
WITH ONE OF THOSE GUYS
I'M ( BLEEP ) CRAZY.
>> HE JUST BROUGHT IN
THE RACE CARD.
>> Jeff: ANDREA ALSO CAME
UNDER FIRE WHEN SHE CONTINUED
TO SHOW AN ATTACHMENT TO MATT.
>> ANDREA STILL HAS A SOFT SPOT
FOR MATT
SO IT JUST MAKES SENSE
TO GET HER OUT.
>> Jeff: BUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THEY TOOK OUT RALPH,
AND IN A SECOND, SURPRISE VOTE,
THE OMETEPE SIX DID WHAT
FEW ALLIANCES HAVE DONE BEFORE--
STEVE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN--
STICK TOGETHER
FROM THE BEGINNING
AND DECIMATE AN ENTIRE TRIBE.
NOW THEY FACE THEIR MOST
FEARSOME ENEMY YET--
EACH OTHER-- AND STEVE AND RALPH
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
WHERE THEY WILL FACE
MIKE AND MATT
IN THE FIRST-EVER FOUR-WAY DUEL.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> RALPH!
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
>> THERE HE IS.
HOW ARE YOU, MAN?
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON?
ME AND STEVE FIGHTING WITH
PHILLIP FOR A LITTLE RICE
AND ALL THAT GOOD STUFF.
I BET YOU STEVE LOST 40 POUNDS.
>> PROBABLY.
>> I MEAN, HE'S PITIFUL.
HE DIDN'T THINK HE WAS
GOING TO MAKE IT
BACK TO CAMP TODAY
AFTER THE GAME.
>> WOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HEY.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GUYS GOT ROOM
FOR ONE MORE?
>> STEVE!
>> WHAT UP, BROTHER!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
( LAUGHTER )
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
REDEMPTION ISLAND
KEEPS ON GETTING
CRAZIER AND CRAZIER.
>> LORDY ME!
>> WE'VE GOT THE THREE REMAINING
ZAPATERA HERE
AT REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AND MATT.
>> I'VE MISSED YOU, MAN.
>> IT'S JUST SO NICE TO SEE
THREE OF THE REALLY
FRIENDLY FACES COMPARED
TO THE OMETEPE TRIBE.
I JUST DID NOT WANT TO GO
BACK THERE TONIGHT.
>> SIX OMETEPE LEFT.
>> WOW.
>> WHAT ARE THEY
GOING TO DO NOW?
>> THE JURY IS GOING TO BE
ALL ZAPATERA.
>> ALL ZAPATERA.
>> JULIE, DAVID, MYSELF,
MATT, RALPH, STEVE.
THAT'S SIX RIGHT THERE.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> I SEE DAYLIGHT AHEAD NOW.
IF ONE OF US ZAPATERA GUYS
GETS INTO THE TOP THREE,
WE'VE GOT THIS THING WON.
AND I WANT TO BE THAT GUY.
SO I'M GOING TO GIVE IT
ALL I'VE GOT.
>> YEAH, YEAH!
>> WHOOO!
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL
WAS PRETTY MUCH AMAZING
BECAUSE IN ONE TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WE GOT RID
OF THE REMAINING TWO ZAPATERA
TRIBE MEMBERS
SO NOW IT'S JUST
THE OMETEPE SIX.
>> OMETEPE!
>> IT IS A LITTLE SCARY THAT NOW
WE HAVE TO TAKE OUT
ONE OF OUR OWN,
BUT IT'S ALSO A LITTLE
EXCITING
BECAUSE FOR THE LAST,
WHAT, FIVE VOTES
WE'VE BEEN ON CRUISE CONTROL
SO NOW WE CAN ACTUALLY
GET INTO THE GAME
OF WHICH I'M EXCITED.
>> HEY, NAT, YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> IS IT HAPPY TEARS OR SAD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S HORMONE TEARS.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> I THINK I STARTED GETTING
KIND OF EMOTIONAL
JUST BECAUSE NOW WE
HAVE TO START
KNOCKING EVERYBODY OFF,
AND FROM THERE, IT JUST,
LIKE, STARTED THINKING
ABOUT HOME
AND MISSING MY FAMILY,
MISSING MY FRIENDS,
MISSING REGULAR LIFE.
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU TO THINK
I'M CRYING BECAUSE I'M--
LIKE I DON'T WANT
TO BE HERE OR ANYTHING.
IT JUST HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH--
>> YOU'RE JUST HAVING A MOMENT?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN TIMES
OUT HERE WHERE NATALIE
HAS JUST BEEN MATURE
BEYOND HER YEARS
AND THEN THERE HAVE BEEN
OTHER TIMES WHEN,
YOU KNOW,
HER YOUTH JUST SHOWS THROUGH.
SHE'S 19.
YOU KNOW, BEING OUT HERE
FOR 30 DAYS,
IT TAKES ITS TOLL ON YOU.
AND IT'S CRITICAL FOR ME
TO COMFORT HER.
I MEAN, SHE'S MY MAIN ALLIANCE
IN THIS GAME,
AND I WANT TO MAKE SURE
SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE CONCERNED ABOUT YOU,
AND WE CARE ABOUT YOU,
AND, YOU KNOW, WHEN WE
SEE YOU ALL OF A SUDDEN
START TO CRY FOR NO REASON,
WE WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S WRONG.
I'VE GOT EIGHT DAYS LEFT,
EIGHT DAYS.
I'VE JUST GOT TO KEEP
EVERYBODY HAPPY,
AND AS LONG AS THEY DON'T
START TALKING TO EACH OTHER
AND REALIZE THAT I'M THE ONE
THAT SHOULD BE GOING,
I'LL BE ALL SE SET.
>> TREE MAIL!
SPRINT OPEN FIRST.
>> OH, MY GOD!
IS THIS FAMILY?
>> WE GOT TREE MAIL THIS MORNING
AND WE GOT A BOX,
AND ON THE TOP OF THE BOX
IT SAID "SPRINT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE JOKING ME
RIGHT NOW.
>> CELL PHONES, BABY!
>> "ANOTHER GOT VOTED OUT
BUT ARE THEY OUT FOR SURE?
COME TO THE ARENA AND SEE
WHO WILL LEAVE
AND WHO WILL ENDURE.
FIRST, CHECK VIDEOS
FOR A SURPRISE."
>> YEAH!
>> NO!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WE GOT, LIKE, A MESSAGE
ABOUT THE DUEL
WHICH WE KIND OF DISCARDED
BECAUSE THEN IT SAID,
"CHECK VIDEOS."
>> EVERYBODY BE QUIET.
>> HI, I'M TRACY, NATALIE'S MOM.
IT'S HARD THAT YOU'VE BEEN
GONE SO LONG,
AND I'M SO PROUD OF YOU
THAT YOU STUCK THIS OUT,
AND WE ALL MISS YOU.
DADDY'S VERY PROUD OF YOU.
I HOPE THAT YOU ARE STRONG.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
>> NATALIE WAS A LITTLE
UPSET, YOU KNOW,
AFTER WE GOT OUT OF TRIBAL.
AND IT WAS PERFECT TIMING
FOR HER
AND REALLY FOR ALL OF US.
>> MY DADDY!
>> HI, ANDREA, WE ALL MISS YOU.
YOUR SISTERS CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN GONE
SO LONG.
WE'LL SEE YOU SOON.
>> OH!
>> BEAUTIFUL!
>> I'M TRACY, PHILLIP'S SISTER.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU
HOW PROFOUNDLY I MISS YOU.
WE ARE ALL THINKING ABOUT YOU.
WE'RE ON YOUR SIDE.
>> HEY, ROB.
WE ARE SO PROUD OF YOU.
YOU HAVE MADE IT SO FAR.
MOM AND DAD SEND THEIR LOVE.
STAY STRONG.
YOU'VE DONE A GREAT JOB.
WE'RE SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> GRANT.
>> THAT'S MY SISTER'S HUSBAND.
>> YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT ADRIEN,
SHE IS NEWLY PREGNANT.
GOOD LUCK.
WIN THIS GAME, AND COME HOME.
>> HEY, ASHLEY!
OH, MY GOSH.
WE ALL MISS YOU SO MUCH, HONEY.
LOVE YOU AND COME HOME SAFE
TO US, SWEETHEART.
HANG IN THERE.
>> OH!
>> COME HERE!
>> IT'S DAY 31, AND, LIKE,
YOU FEEL EXHAUSTED,
BUT WHEN YOU HEAR FROM HOME,
IT JUST LIFTS
YOUR SPIRITS SO MUCH.
AND IT WAS A REALLY,
REALLY GOOD SURPRISE.
>> SPRINT 4G,
FOLLOW THE PATH TO THE ARENA
WHERE YOU WILL COMPETE
IN A DUEL.
CHECK VIDEOS FOR A SURPRISE.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS!
THE VIDEOS!
TREE MAIL TODAY, I THOUGHT IT
WAS JUST GOING TO BE
WALK OUT THERE,
MAYBE GET A NOTE TO A DUEL.
BUT OH!
WE'RE GOING TO GET TO SEE VIDEOS
OF OUR LOVED ONES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HEY, RALPH.
HAVING A GOOD TIME?
I WANT YOU TO KNOW WE ALL
MISS YOU HERE AT HOME.
ALL THE COWS ARE DOING GREAT.
A COUPLE OF THE CHICKENS
GOT KILLED, THOUGH.
HOPE YOU'RE NOT UPSET
ABOUT THAT.
WE'RE REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU BACK HOME.
>> THAT'S AWESOME!
>> WE ALL MISS YOU
AND HOPE THAT YOU ARE--
YOU ARE WELL,
AND YOU ARE SAFE.
>> I'VE NEVER GONE FOR 31 DAYS
WITHOUT BEING ABLE
TO SPEAK TO ANY OF MY FAMILY,
EVEN WHEN I WAS IN
THE MARINE CORPS.
WE COULD STILL REACH OUT
VIA E-MAIL.
SO IT WAS REALLY TOUCHING
TO SEE A MESSAGE FROM MY MOM.
LOVE YOU, MOM.
>> HEY, BROTHER,
JUST WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT THE FOLKS ARE WISHING
ALL THE LOVE FOR YOU.
WE'RE THINKING A LOT ABOUT YOU.
I'M GOING TO GET EMOTIONAL HERE.
A BIG STEAK AND COLD BEERS
ARE ON ME
NEXT TIME WE SEE EACH OTHER.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> HEY, MATT.
I JUST WANT TO SAY LOVE YOU.
I HOPE YOU'RE HEALTHY.
I HOPE YOU'RE STAYING STRONG.
>> I JUST SEE MY BROTHER
AND I'M JUST THINKING--
I JUST WANT TO DIE RIGHT THERE,
JUST SEEING HIM.
>> WE ALL LOVE YOU
AND MISS YOU LIKE CRAZY.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU VERY SOON.
>> IT MAKES EVERY STRUGGLE,
EVERY HARD TIME
I'VE GONE THROUGH
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND
COMPLETELY WORTH IT.
>> THREE, TWO...
THAT'S IT.
IF THERE'S A CHANCE
THAT I CAN SPEND
ANY TIME WITH ME BROTHER,
I WILL DO ANYTHING I CAN
TO WIN TODAY.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS
FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
MATT, MIKE, RALPH, AND STEVE.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> Jeff: THIS MORNING
IN TREE MAIL,
BOTH CAMPS RECEIVED
THE EPIC 4G, ONLY FROM SPRINT.
I WILL TAKE THE PHONES BACK.
GRANT.
SO LOVE FROM HOME
ON A SPRINT PHONE
IS PRETTY NICE.
THAT'S WHAT WE LEARNED.
LOVE IN PERSON
WILL BE EVEN BETTER.
>> DON'T DO THIS.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER
OF TODAY'S DUEL
WILL GET THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SPEND SOME TIME
WITH THEIR LOVED ONE IN PERSON.
FIRST, YOU GOTTA WIN THE DUEL.
IT IS A FOUR-PERSON DUEL,
FIRST TIME WE'VE HAD
ONE OF THESE.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
YOU EACH HAVE FOUR TILES.
EACH ROUND, YOU WILL TOSS A BALL
TRYING TO BREAK A TILE.
THE FIRST THREE PEOPLE TO BREAK
ALL THEIR TILES STAY ALIVE
IN THIS GAME.
THE LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD,
THEIR QUEST FOR THE MONEY
IS OVER.
IN ADDITION, THE FIRST PERSON
TO FINISH THIS CHALLENGE
WINS LOVE FROM HOME.
( APPLAUSE )
THERE IS A LOT AT STAKE.
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT, TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
LET'S GO.
THE WAY THIS WILL WORK,
YOU'LL THROW,
ONE PERSON AT A TIME, IN ROUNDS.
MATT, YOU'RE UP FIRST.
MATT A LITTLE CHIP,
THAT WON'T DO IT.
MIKE.
MIKE ONE TOSS,
BREAKS HIS FIRST TILE.
RALPH MAKES A TOSS, VERY CLOSE.
STEVE SHORT.
AT THE END OF THE FIRST ROUND,
MIKE HAS ONE.
EVERYBODY ELSE NOTHING.
MATT, YOU'RE UP.
MATT BREAKS A TILE.
MIKE BREAKS HIS SECOND TILE.
RALPH BREAKS A TILE.
STEVE BREAKS A TILE.
AT THE END OF THIS ROUND,
MIKE HAS TWO TILES BROKEN.
EVERYBODY ELSE HAS
ONE TILE BROKEN.
MATT, YOU'RE UP.
MATT BREAKS HIS SECOND TILE.
TYING HIM WITH MIKE.
MIKE BREAKS HIS THIRD TILE.
RALPH BREAKS HIS SECOND TILE.
STEVE JUST MISSES.
HERE'S WHERE WE STAND NOW.
MIKE HAS THREE TILES BROKEN.
MATT HAS TWO BROKEN.
RALPH HAS TWO BROKEN,
AND STEVE HAS ONE BROKEN.
MATT, YOU'RE UP.
OH!
JUST MISSES.
MIKE COULD WIN
THE DUEL RIGHT HERE.
AND HE DOES!
MIKE NOT ONLY STAYS ALIVE
IN THIS GAME
AND ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
MIKE HAS JUST WON THE
OPPORTUNITY
FOR FOR SOME IN-PERSON,
UP-CLOSE LOVE FROM FAMILY.
IT IS NOW DOWN TO MATT,
RALPH, AND STEVE.
TWO MORE PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO STAY ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
ONE OF YOU WILL BE GOING HOME.
RALPH, YOU'RE UP.
JUST MISSES.
STEVE.
TAKE YOUR SHOT.
STEVE SHORT AGAIN.
MATT HAS TWO TILES BROKEN.
LOOKING FOR A THIRD.
AND HE GETS IT.
RALPH HAS TWO TILES BROKEN.
HE'S LOOKING FOR A THIRD.
AND HE GETS IT.
STEVE NEEDS TO GET
A SECOND ONE RIGHT HERE.
AND HE DOESN'T.
MATT AND RALPH BOTH ONLY HAVE
ONE TILE LEFT TO BREAK.
MATT STAYS ALIVE.
HE JOINS MIKE.
RALPH, BREAK THIS TILE.
YOU STAY ALIVE.
AND HE DOES.
RALPH WILL LIVE TO SEE
ANOTHER DAY
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THE JOURNEY FOR STEVE
HAS COME TO AN END.
MIKE, FIRST OF ALL,
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: SURVIVING ANOTHER
DUEL AND WINNING SOME LOVE.
STEVE, UNFORTUNATELY,
THE GAME IS OVER,
BUT YOU ARE NOT GOING HOME.
YOU ARE GOING TO BE
A MEMBER OF THE JURY.
TAKE YOUR BUFF.
PUT IT IN THE URN.
SEE YOU AT THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
( APPLAUSE )
>> BYE, STEVE.
>> Jeff: NOW TO THE REWARD
PART OF THIS DUEL.
MIKE, COME ON OVER HERE.
SO AS PART OF WINNING THIS DUEL,
YOU HAVE WON
TIME WITH YOUR LOVED ONE,
YOUR MOM, JANE.
LET'S BRING HER OUT.
HOW'S SHE LOOK?
>> AMAZING, AS ALWAYS.
>> Jeff: SO YOUR MOM
IS 10 FEET AWAY.
BUT BEFORE YOU GUYS EMBRACE,
YOU HAVE A DECISION TO MAKE.
IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN FORGO
YOUR OWN LOVE WITH YOUR MOM,
AND INSTEAD YOU COULD TRY TO BUY
SOME GOOD WILL
IN A JURY SITUATION
SHOULD YOU BE THE ONE
THAT REENTERS THE GAME
BY GIVING THE LOVE INSTEAD
TO THE TWO GUYS
YOU'VE BEEN LIVING WITH
OUT HERE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> WHAT'S UP!
>> Jeff: THERE'S MATT'S
BROTHER BURTON,
AND RALPH'S BUDDY, RONNIE.
( APPLAUSE )
>> RALPH.
>> Jeff: THAT'S YOUR
FIRST CHOICE.
YOUR SECOND CHOICE
IS YOU CAN INSTEAD GIVE LOVE
TO EVERYBODY LEFT IN THIS GAME.
>> OH!
>> THERE'S ANDREA'S DAD.
THERE'S GRANT'S BROTHER-IN-LAW.
STEVE.
THAT LOOKS LIKE ROB'S SISTER,
HEATHER.
THERE'S NATALIE'S MOM.
TRACY.
PHILLIP'S SISTER, TRACY.
AND ASHLEY'S MOM, TERRY.
SO, MIKE, VERY BIG
POTENTIALLY
MILLION-DOLLAR DECISION.
TAKE ME THROUGH
THE THOUGHT PROCESS.
>> THE DECISION
IS ALMOST CLEAR IN MY HEAD.
YESTERDAY, I WAS READING
IT WAS EITHER MATTHEW OR MARK,
AND JESUS WAS ASKED
OF ALL THE COMMANDMENTS,
WHAT ARE THE GREATEST?
AND HE RESPONDED,
"LOVE YOUR BROTHER
LIKE YOU WOULD LOVE YOURSELF."
SO I THINK IF I GIVE
THE MOST GOOD
TO THE MOST PEOPLE
AND MAKE FRIENDS FROM ENEMIES,
I THINK THAT'S
THE ONLY PLAY HERE.
>> Jeff: LET ME MAKE SURE
I'M CLEAR ON WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU'RE GIVING UP YOUR LOVE
WITH YOUR MOM,
AND YOU'RE GIVING UP THE LOVE
FOR RALPH AND MATT,
AND YOU ARE GIVING IT
TO THE SIX PEOPLE
WHO SINGLEHANDEDLY
DECIMATED YOUR TRIBE.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: I GOTTA TELL YOU,
I THOUGHT THE ODDS
OF THAT HAPPENING
WERE LESS THAN ZERO.
JANE, DOES THIS DECISION
SURPRISE YOU?
>> NO.
THIS IS WHO MY SON IS.
HE IS A HERO.
HONEY, I'M SO VERY PROUD OF YOU.
>> SEE YOU SOON.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JANE,
BURTON, RONNIE,
TIME FOR YOU GUYS TO HEAD OUT.
>> MATT, STAY STRONG.
LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, HONEY.
>> SEE YOU SOON.
>> OKAY.
>> BYE, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO,
YOU'VE MADE A HUGE DECISION
IN THE GAME.
I HOPE IT PAYS OFF FOR YOU.
MIKE, MATT, RALPH,
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK AND AWAIT NEWS
OF YOUR NEXT DUEL.
>> THANK YOU, MIKE.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
DON'T VOTE ME OFF AGAIN.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jeff: ONLY ONE THING
LEFT TO DO--
JOIN YOUR LOVED ONES.
YOU GUYS WILL HEAD BACK TO CAMP
AND SPEND THE AFTERNOON
TOGETHER.
>> TODAY I WOULD HAVE ACCEPTED
IF MIKE WOULD HAVE
KEPT HIS MOTHER
AND HUNG AROUND WITH HER
THE REST OF THE EVENING,
NO HARD FEELINGS WHATSOEVER.
BUT I'M SURE HE'S LOOKING
FOR WINNING A MILLION DOLLARS
AND WAS HOPING TO PULL IN
MORE VOTES,
SO HE LET FAMILY SEE THEM SIX
AND THAT REALLY PISSED ME OFF.
THAT WAS VERY HARD, MIKE.
YOU HAVE THE OLD FEATHER
IN THE GAME.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
>> IT'S NOT.
>> IT SUCKED.
>> I THINK IT WAS
KIND OF STUPID,
HIM AND THE GOOD LORD,
WHATEVER.
HE SAID THAT'S THE WAY
HE WANTED TO DO IT.
THAT'S SOMETHING
HE HAS TO LIVE WITH.
BUT IF I HAD BEEN IN HIS SHOES,
I WOULD HAVE SPENT IT
WITH MY MOM.
>> MIKE, I'M GLAD I DIDN'T WIN
BECAUSE I COULDN'T
HAVE DONE THAT.
I MEAN--
>> THE WAY THEY TREATED ME--
>> YEAH, I MEAN, SERIOUSLY,
ME, TOO.
>> I WOULDN'T HAVE
GIVEN IT TO THEM.
>> I ASKED GOD TO HELP ME WIN
AND I THINK THAT'S WHAT
HE ASKED OF ME.
THE DECISION I MADE TODAY
WAS NOT A STRATEGIC ONE.
IT WASN'T TO EARN
THE GOOD GRACES
OF THE OMETEPE TRIBE.
IT WAS JUST
THE RIGHT DECISION TO MAKE
AND THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
IF I MAKE IT DEEP INTO THIS GAME
AND IT EARNS ME
A VOTE OR TWO ON THE JURY,
THEN THAT WILL BE A GREAT BONUS.
I'M SORRY, GUYS.
>> NO, NO, DON'T BE SORRY.
MAN, THAT'S MORE THAN I'VE DONE
THE WHOLE TIME
I'VE BEEN OUT HERE,
JUST THAT ONE MOMENT, YOU KNOW.
>> I FEEL BAD FOR MATT
AND HIS BROTHER,
RALPH AND HIS FRIEND,
BUT I'VE APOLOGIZED
TO THEM FOR THAT.
THAT'S THE BEST I CAN DO,
AND IT'S HARD FOR ME KNOW
I'VE LET MY FRIENDS DOWN,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IT IS WHAT IT IS AT THIS POINT.
( CHEERS )
>> THIS IS OUR SHELTER.
>> I'LL SHOW YOU WHERE WE SLEEP.
>> WALKING INTO CAMP WITH OUR
LOVED ONES FEELS SO SURREAL.
I GOT TO SHOW MY MOM
WHERE I'VE BEEN LIVING,
AND IT WAS JUST
LIKE EVERYTHING I NEEDED,
AND SO MUCH MORE.
>> I KEEP THE CALENDAR
EVERY DAY.
>> OH WOW.
>> I MARK IT OFF.
LIKE, YESTERDAY, WAS 30.
>> EVERYBODY SAYS,
"TELL HIM WE LOVE HIM!"
>> OKAY.
>> TELL HIM WE'RE SO PROUD.
>> COOL.
>> HOW DO YOU KEEP
YOUR HAIR SO NICE?
IT'S LOOKING GREAT.
YOU'RE WASTING MONEY
ALL THESE YEARS.
>> ADRIEN SENDS HER LOVE.
SHE WISHES SHE COULD BE HERE.
I WISH EVERYBODY
SHOULD SEE THIS.
>> IT'S SO MOTIVATING,
ACTUALLY PHYSICALLY
SEEING SOMEBODY
AND HEARING THEM TALK TO YOU
AND BEING ABLE TO LOOK
INTO THEIR EYES,
IT'S PRICELESS, MAN.
>> I'M FINE.
>> I KNOW.
>> I HAVE NEVER BEEN
AWAY FROM HOME
MORE THAN TWO WEEKS.
I'VE TALKED TO MY MOM EVERY DAY,
SO IT WAS JUST GOOD TO SEE HER
AND FOR HER TO TELL ME
HOW SHE'S PROUD OF ME
AND HOW MY FAMILY
IS DOING BACK HOME.
AND IT JUST MADE ME FEEL
LIKE I--
I CAN DO IT, AND I CAN PUSH
THROUGH THE NEXT SEVEN,
EIGHT DAYS.
>> THIS IS A SOCIAL GAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'M PREPARED TO GO CRAZY
IF I HAVE TO.
THAT'S WHAT WORKS FOR ME,
YOU KNOW.
JUST SEEING MY SISTER
AND SEEING HER CONFIDENCE IN ME
EMPOWERED ME AND RENEWED ME
AT ANOTHER LEVEL
TO CONTINUE TO DOMINATE.
CONTINUE TO DOMINATE.
AND BE WHO I AM.
>> PHILLIP'S A NUT JOB.
HE'S A WHACKO, BUT HE'S,
LIKE, THE BIGGEST GOAT.
HE'S PISSED EVERYBODY HERE OFF.
>> OH, REALLY.
>> IF I DRAG HIM TO THE END,
HE DOESN'T GET ANY VOTES.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW?
BUT YOU HAVE TO, LIKE, ALWAYS
ADJUST YOUR STRATEGY DAY BY DAY.
GRANT THINKS IT'S ME AND HIM.
NATALIE THINKS IT'S ME AND HER.
ALL THEY HAVE TO DO
IS TALK TO EACH OTHER,
BUT THEY WON'T, YOU KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE RIGHT NOW
I'M PLAYING MY BEST GAME,
BUT EVEN EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED
UP UNTIL RIGHT NOW,
MEANS NOTHING
UNLESS I CAN FINISH IT.
I NEED THIS.
IT'S TO MAKE A BETTER LIFE
FOR MY WIFE AND MY KIDS.
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE AT A POINT NOW
WHERE SOME PEOPLE MIGHT BE
TAKING A BREAK FROM THE GAME
AND THINKING ABOUT HOME,
IT JUST MAKES ME FOCUS.
I WANT TO WIN "SURVIVOR."
THIS IS SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO DO
FOR 10 YEARS NOW.
I'M EIGHT DAYS AWAY.
SO THERE'S NOTHING
THAT'S GOING TO STOP ME.
>> BA-DA-BUM!
GOOD MORNING, TREE MAIL.
RISE AND SHINE.
IT SAYS, "FEELING PRESSURED
TO STEP IT UP?
IS STRATEGY ON THE RISE?
IT'S AN UPHILL BATTLE,
NO MATTER HOW YOU TREAD
WHEN IMMUNITY IS THE PRIZE."
>> THERE'S THREE IN A ROW.
>> THIS MORNING WE GOT
TREE MAIL,
LOOKS LIKE ANOTHER
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
BUT TONIGHT, I FEEL LIKE IT'S
NOT GOING TO BE TOO DIFFICULT.
THERE'S JUST ONE PERSON
THAT CAN'T WIN TODAY.
THE VOTE WILL PROBABLY GO
TOWARDS ANDREA.
SHE'S GREAT AT THE CHALLENGES,
AND STRATEGICALLY,
SHE PROBABLY KNOWS MORE
ABOUT THIS GAME
THAN EVERYONE
EXCEPT GRANT AND I.
THEREFORE, SHE'S GOT TO GO.
MY SISTER GAVE ME A SHIRT
WITH AMBER AND MY DAUGHTER,
LUCIA, ON IT,
AND I'M GOING TO WORK
MY ASS OFF TO MAKE SURE
ANDREA DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
LOOKS A LITTLE DAUNTING?
>> A LITTLE BIT.
>> Jeff: GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> WE ARE.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
MARIANO,
ONCE AGAIN, I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU ARE GOING TO RACE
TO COLLECT A SERIES
OF PUZZLE STEPS.
YOU MUST THEN PLACE
THE STEPS IN ORDER
FROM BOTTOM TO TOP,
COMPLETING A VERY TALL
STAIRCASE.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH
THEIR STAIRCASE AND GET
TO THE TOP WINS IMMUNITY
AND IS SAFE AT THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I KNOW IT'S WORTH PLAYING FOR.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
WHATEVER YOU HAVE IN YOUR TANK
YOU NEED TO USE RIGHT NOW.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU HAVE
TO UNTIE THE KNOTS.
THEN YOU HAVE TO GET THESE
PUZZLE STEPS TO YOUR PLANK.
THEN YOU'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
WHICH ONE GOES FIRST.
ROB'S GOT HIS FIRST BOARD IN.
GRANT HAS ONE IN.
ANDREA'S IN IT.
IF YOU'RE WRONG,
YOU'VE GOT TO GO BACK DOWN.
YOU CAN ONLY BRING
ONE PLANK AT A TIME.
YOU'VE GOT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING
OR YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE TIME.
ANDREA IN THE LEAD.
SHE'S MOVING ON TO HER
SECOND SET OF STEPS.
ROB HAS HIS FIRST SET.
GRANT FINISHES HIS FIRST SET.
ASHLEY GOING TO FINISH UP
HER FIRST SET.
PHILLIP IS GOING VERY SLOW.
NATALIE HAVING NO LUCK AT ALL.
IT IS ROB, GRANT, AND ANDREA
WORKING ON THEIR SECOND SET
OF PUZZLE STEPS.
GRANT'S WRONG.
HE HEADS BACK DOWN.
ANDREA HAS HER FIRST STEP.
ROB HAS HIS FIRST STEP
OF THE SECOND SET.
ASHLEY STRUGGLING
TO STAY IN THIS.
GRANT HAS HIS FIRST BOARD.
ANDREA NOW IN THE LEAD
WITH HER SECOND BOARD.
ROB PICKED THE WRONG BOARD.
GOTTA GO BACK DOWN.
IT IS ANDREA AND GRANT
RIGHT NOW.
YOU NEED TO PICK IT UP
IF YOU WANT TO WIN!
SECOND PLACE BUYS YOU NOTHING
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> NO!
>> Jeff: ANDREA WITH A BIG
MISTAKE.
SHE GRABBED THE WRONG BOARD.
IT IS ROB AND GRANT NOW.
GRANT HAS HIS SECOND SET
FINISHED.
IT'S ABOUT 110 DEGREES TODAY.
ADDING TO THE DIFFICULTY.
ROB HAS COMPLETED
HIS SECOND SET.
GRANT HAS COMPLETED
GRANT WORKING ON THE THIRD,
AND FINAL SET OF PUZZLE STEPS.
ANDREA'S COMPLETED
HER SECOND SET.
PHILLIP, ASHLEY, NATALIE,
HAVE FALLEN OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
GRANT IS WRONG.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE
TO HEAD BACK DOWN.
ONCE AGAIN,
THE LEAD COULD CHANGE.
ROB HAS IT RIGHT!
ANDREA HAS HERS RIGHT!
GRANT IS WRONG AGAIN!
TWO MISTAKES FOR GRANT.
OPENING THE DOOR FOR ROB
AND ANDREA.
ANDREA HAS HER SECOND BOARD,
GRANT HAS HIS FIRST BOARD.
ROB STRUGGLING
TO GET UP THESE STEPS.
HE IS LITERALLY CARRYING
HIS FAMILY ON HIS BACK!
GRANT NOW MAKING UP GROUND.
GRANT HAS HIS SECOND BOARD.
ROB HAS HIS THIRD BOARD.
ANDREA RIGHT BEHIND.
ANDREA'S GOING TO NEED
A MISTAKE FROM ROB.
GRANT HAS HIS THIRD BOARD.
ROB HAS HIS FOURTH BOARD
IN PLACE.
ROB HAS TWO STEPS LEFT.
GRANT HAS THREE,
ANDREA HAS THREE.
IT IS GRANT AND ROB.
TIED.
BOTH WITH TWO STEPS LEFT.
ANDREA NOW WITH TWO STEPS LEFT.
ROB HIS LEGS NEARLY BUCKLING,
CRAWLING UP THESE STEPS.
ROB HAS ONE STEP LEFT!
GRANT HAS TWO!
ANDREA RIGHT BEHIND.
AS LONG AS ROB CAN GET UP,
HE WILL WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
GRANT HAS ONE STEP LEFT.
ANDREA, SHE'S GOT ONE STEP LEFT.
ROB WITH HIS LAST PUZZLE STEP.
STRUGGLING TO MAKE IT UP
WITHOUT COLLAPSING.
32 DAYS OF EXHAUSTION
SETTING IN.
GRANT RACING TO THE TOP.
THIS IS IT.
ROB CRAWLS TO THE TOP.
MARIANO WINS IMMUNITY!
GREAT EFFORT FROM EVERYBODY.
YOU ALL RIGHT, ROB?
>> IT'S HOT.
MY LEGS ARE BURNING.
I'LL LIVE, DUDE.
LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: NO, NO, NO,
RELAX, MAN.
>> SOME WATER?
>> Jeff: GOT IT?
ARE YOU CRAMPING?
>> YEAH.
>> OH!
GOD HELP ME.
>> Jeff: DO YOU WANT ME
TO HAVE MEDICAL LOOK AT YOU?
>> NO.
I THINK IF I COULD STAND,
IT WOULD BE BETTER.
>> HEY, COULD YOU GUYS
HELP ME STAND UP?
YEAH, THAT'S BETTER.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
WE'LL GO BACK TO CAMP.
>> Jeff: MARIANO,
CAN YOU HOBBLE OVER HERE?
>> YES.
( APPLAUSE )
>> WAY TO GO, ROB!
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN,
BARELY STANDING,
MARIANO SAFE AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU,
AFTER 32 DAYS TOGETHER
IN ONE SOLID GROUP OF SIX,
THIS ALLIANCE IS ABOUT
TO BE BROKEN UP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
>> THANKS.
( APPLAUSE )
>> OH, MAN, MY LEGS
ARE LIKE JELL-O.
>> I KNOW.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS LIKE--
I COULDN'T BREATHE, YOU KNOW?
PHYSICALLY, THE CHALLENGE,
I HAD TO LITERALLY
GIVE EVERYTHING I HAD.
AFTERWARDS,
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO DIE.
BUT I FIGURE,
I'M SEVEN DAYS AWAY.
AND I'M GIVING IT
EVERYTHING I GOT.
ONE OF US HAS TO GO
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I MEAN, THAT'S A FACT.
THERE ARE TWO MAIN THINGS
THAT I GAIN FROM WINNING
IMMUNITY TODAY.
NUMBER ONE, I'M NOT GOING HOME
NO MATTER WHAT.
AND NUMBER TWO,
ALL MY OPTIONS ARE OPEN,
AND I CAN DECIDE
WHO'S GOING HOME.
>> SO WE'RE ALL GOOD, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, RIGHT?
>> TONIGHT WE'RE GOING
TO VOTE OFF ANDREA.
SHE'S ONE OF THE STRONGEST
COMPETITORS
IN THE CHALLENGES,
PLUS HER RELATIONSHIP
WITH MATT ON REDEMPTION ISLAND
IS STILL A THREAT.
>> ARE WE VOTING PHILLIP?
IS THAT THE PLAN?
LIKE, FOR SURE?
>> YEAH.
>> IT WILL BE A SHOCK
TO HER, I THINK,
BUT THERE IS NO MORE
ZAPATERA LEFT AT CAMP.
SO SHE NEEDS TO GO.
>> SHE HAS NO IDEA.
SHE'S NOT GOING
TO SEE IT COMING.
>> LOVERS ARE GOING
TO BE REUNITED.
>> PHILLIP, SOMEBODY'S GOING
TO COME BACK FROM REDEMPTION,
AND I DON'T WANT THEM
SLEEPING NEXT TO ME.
>> THERE'S PLENTY DOWN
ON THE SIDE THERE.
THEY'LL HAVE TO PATCH IT UP.
>> WE'RE ALL COMPLETELY SET
ON GETTING RID OF ANDREA,
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN,
PHILLIP REGAINS HIS SPOT
IN OUR TRIBE
AS ANNOYANCE NUMBER ONE.
HE STARTED DRIVING
EVERYONE CRAZY.
>> THERE'S A WASP NEAR YOU,
BE CAREFUL.
DON'T MOVE YOUR ARMS SO QUICKLY.
>> DON'T YELL AT ME!
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO TELL YOU
WHEN YOU DO
QUICK ACTIONS AROUND THEM
THAT UPSETS THEM.
>> I'M NOT STUPID.
>> WELL, YOU WERE MOVING
YOUR ARMS QUICKLY.
>> STRAIGHT BACK
TO NORMAL FELIPE.
>> I'M TELLING YOU MAN,
THAT FEELING IN MY STOMACH
HASN'T CHANGED SINCE DAY ONE.
>> I COULD BE WRONG,
BUT I'M NOT CONCERNED
ABOUT GOING HOME TONIGHT
BECAUSE EARLY ON IN THE GAME,
I MADE MYSELF THE VILLAIN.
SO THAT EVERYONE
IN MY TRIBE FEELS
THAT THEIR BEST CHANCE
OF WINNING
AGAINST ANYBODY IS ME.
IT'S BRILLIANT STRATEGY,
AND I NEED TO KIND OF PUT
A LITTLE SALT ON THAT WOUND
EVERY NOW AND THEN
TO MAKE SURE FOLKS
DON'T FORGET THAT.
THESE FISHNETS REMAINED
IN PLACE,
THE ENTIRE TIME.
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
BOTH OF THEM END UP LIKE THIS.
YOU MANGLED MY NET.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOUR ROOF?
THE HELL YOU SAY?
I THINK ROB FEELS VERY STRONGLY
THAT IF IT'S HIM AND I
IN THE FINAL,
THAT HE CAN WIN
THE MILLION DOLLARS.
BUT I HAVE AN ORAL ARGUMENT
THAT NOBODY HERE ON MY TRIBE,
INCLUDING HIM,
HAS THOUGHT OF IT.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT TO SAY
TO MAKE EVERYBODY THINK TWICE
ABOUT VOTING FOR HIM,
REGARDLESS OF
EVERYTHING ELSE I'VE SAID.
HONESTLY,
I THINK I COULD DEFEAT ROB.
>> DUDE, WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE, RIGHT?
WE GET RID OF ANDREA TONIGHT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T WANT TO ROCK THE BOAT,
BUT I'M THINKING
MAYBE WE SHOULD
VOTE OUT PHILLIP.
IT'S JUST THAT SINCE DAY ONE,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVEN'T TRUSTED.
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU,
I'M HAVING SOME SECOND THOUGHTS
AS TO WHO I WANT
TO SIT THERE WITH AT THE END.
IF I WERE TO KEEP
PHILLIP AROUND,
HE'S TERRIBLE IN CHALLENGES.
AND HE'S A GOAT, PERFECT PERSON
TO TAKE TO THE END.
AT THE SAME TIME,
PHILLIP COULD BE PLAYING ME.
HE'S PRETTY GOOD WITH WORDS.
HE'S A GOOD SPEAKER.
SO WHEN IT COMES DOWN
TO THE JURY,
THAT COULD BE A PROBLEM.
IS HE THAT GOOD?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> HAS HE SAID ANYTHING TO YOU?
>> HE HASN'T SAID
ANYTHING AT ALL.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
ANDREA'S A COMPETITTOR.
IF SHE SITS AT THE END
SHE COULD POSSIBLY BEAT ME.
IF I MAKE THE WRONG DECISION,
32 DAYS OF HARD WORK
COULD BE GONE JUST LIKE THAT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
DAVID, JULIE, AND STEVE.
THE TIME HAS FINALLY COME.
AFTER DOMINATING FOR 32 DAYS
AND VOTING EVERYBODY ELSE
OUT OF THIS GAME,
THIS TIGHT GROUP OF SIX
HAS TO VOTE
ONE OF THEIR OWN
OUT OF THIS GAME.
ANDREA, CONCERNED AT ALL
AS WE SIT HERE RIGHT NOW?
>> FOR MYSELF?
>> Jeff: YEAH.
>> I FEEL CONFIDENT
IN THE RELATIONSHIPS
I'VE BUILT WITHIN
THE OMETEPE SIX,
SO I FEEL SAFE TONIGHT.
I MEAN, YOU CAN NEVER
BE CERTAIN IN THIS GAME,
BUT AS OF NOW, I FEEL LIKE
I'M TRUSTING THE RIGHT PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: SO, NATALIE, IS IT
KIND OF EXCITING
TO BE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL?
IS IT TERRIFYING?
>> IT'S A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
IT'S NERVE-RACKING.
IT'S SCARY.
AND IT'S NOT FUN.
IT'S DEFINITELY NOT FUN TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, YOU MADE
A POINT ABOUT SAYING,
"I'M THE SIXTH MAN
ON THIS GROUP,
AND I'M FINE WITH THAT."
WELL, THERE'S ONLY
SIX PEOPLE LEFT.
SO IT SEEMS LIKE THERE'S
A VERY GOOD CHANCE
IT SHOULD BE YOU TONIGHT.
IS THERE ANY PART OF YOU
THAT MIGHT BE LYING DOWN
AND SAYING, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO LOOK
LIKE A THREAT."
BECAUSE YOU AND NATALIE WEREN'T
EVEN COMPETITIVE TODAY.
>> TODAY, IT WAS 110 DEGREES.
I'M A 52-YEAR-OLD MAN.
CLEARLY, ON THAT
PARTICULAR EVENT,
I WAS OUT OF MY LEAGUE.
I'VE BEEN WAITING AND HOPING
THAT WE WOULD DO SOMETHING
THAT REQUIRED
UPPER BODY STRENGTH
BECAUSE WHEN I WENT IN THE ARMY,
AT 29, OUT OF 1500 MEN,
NO MAN COULD OUTRUN ME,
DO MORE PUSH-UPS, MORE SIT-UPS.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP,
I'M MAKING THE ARGUMENT
THE REASON TO
KEEP YOU IS BECAUSE
YOU AREN'T A THREAT
AND YOU RAISE YOUR HAND
AND SAY, "I'M A HUGE THREAT.
I JUST HAVEN'T HAD
THE RIGHT CHALLENGE."
ANDREA, YOU WERE VERY
COMPETITIVE TODAY.
ARE WE AT A POINT
IN THE GAME WHERE ABILITY
TO BE COMPETITIVE STILL
MIGHT MAKE YOU A TARGET
BECAUSE YOU COULD WIN
YOUR WAY TO THE END?
>> I REALIZE THAT IT'S
AN INDIVIDUAL GAME
BUT WE ALSO WANT TO KEEP
OUR TRIBE STRONG
BECAUSE WHOEVER IS COMING
BACK FROM REDEMPTION,
WE NEED TO BEAT THEM.
>> Jeff: SO, GRANT,
ARE YOU HAVING TO PLAY
YOUR OWN PSYCHOLOGICAL GAME
OF THIS IS WHY
YOU SHOULD KEEP ME
AND NOT GET RID OF ME.
>> TO A CERTAIN DEGREE.
I CAME INTO THIS GAME
KNOWING MYSELF
AND THIS IS WHO I AM.
THERE'S ONE THING YOU CAN'T
TAKE AWAY FROM ANYBODY,
IF THEY'RE BEING THEMSELVES,
THEIR TRUE SELVES
YOU CAN TELL
AND IF THEY'RE BEING FAKE,
YOU CAN TELL THAT, TOO,
AND PUTTING ON A FRONT
JUST TO SAY,
"HEY, I WANT A MILLION DOLLARS."
>> Jeff: PHILLIP,
SHARE WITH ME SOME INSIGHT
BASED ON YOUR BACKGROUND
AS COUNTER-INTELLIGENCE,
AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME,
CAN YOU MAKE IT
TO THE END IF YOU ARE TRUTHFUL?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I'LL MAKE THE CASE WITH MYSELF.
I HAVE FORMED NO ALLIANCES
WHERE I, YOU KNOW, BROKE THEM.
I THINK EVERYBODY KNOWS ME
TO BE, YOU KNOW,
THE SENIOR STATESMAN.
I'M A GUY WHO LEADS BY EXAMPLE.
DON'T KNOW FOR SURE, BUT I THINK
I'M A GUY THAT YOU WANT
TO HAVE AROUND.
>> Jeff: HERE'S THE GREAT THING
ABOUT THE VOTE TONIGHT,
UNLESS I'M WRONG, DOES ANYBODY
TRULY FEEL INSECURE
AT THIS MOMENT?
ROB, THAT'S THE PRO AND THE CON
OF WHAT YOU GUYS HAVE BUILT.
THE PRO IS YOU WERE SO SOLID,
YOU WERE ABLE
TO DESTROY ANOTHER TRIBE.
THE CON IS YOU'RE SO SOLID,
SOMEBODY'S ABOUT TO GET
BLINDSIDED.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, AND THIS
IS A TOUGH DECISION TONIGHT,
BUT I FEEL A LOT BETTER
WITH THIS AROUND MY NECK.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU,
HAD GRANT WON THIS TODAY
OR ANYBODY ELSE FOR THAT MATTER,
I WOULD BE FEELING IT.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP,
BEFORE WE VOTE,
SHARE ONE LITTLE NUGGET
THAT YOU THINK
YOUR GREAT-GRANDFATHER
WOULD SAY
IF HE WERE HERE RIGHT NOW.
>> HE'D SAY, "YOU'VE DONE
EVERYTHING RIGHT
TO GET TO THIS POINT.
HOLD THE FAITH."
>> Jeff: OKAY,
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ROB HAS THE NECKLACE.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR ROB.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
NATALIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ANDREA.
PHILLIP.
ANDREA.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: TWO VOTES ANDREA,
ONE VOTE PHILLIP.
>> SHE GOT BLINDSIDED.
>> Jeff: ANDREA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ANDREA,
ONE VOTE PHILLIP.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT.
ANDREA.
THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> TRICKY, TRICKY.
>> Jeff: ANDREA,
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE
TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION.
GOOD LUCK.
WELL, THAT'S ONE BLINDSIDE.
I HAVE A FEELING
IT WON'T BE THE LAST.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME
ON "SURVIVOR":
>> AND THEN THERE WERE FIVE!
>> I LOVE BLINDSIDES.
>> Jeff: THIS CLOSE TO THE END.
>> SPLITTING THEM UP
IS THE BEST ROUTE.
>> KNOW THAT I HAVE YOUR BACK.
ASHLEY CAN'T BE TRUSTED.
>> Jeff: EVERY...
>> THAT IS A SNAKE, BRO.
>> Jeff: MOMENT...
>> I DON'T GIVE A ( BLEEP ).
>> GET OUT OF OUR FACE.
>> Jeff: COUNTS.
>> ONE THING YOU DON'T
WANT TO HAPPEN,
IT HAPPENED.
>> WELL, OBVIOUSLY,
I'M A LITTLE BITTER.
ALL OF THEM, EXCEPT
FOR PHILLIP, YOU KNOW,
LOOKED ME IN THE EYES
AND SAID WE'RE VOTING PHILLIP,
AND SOMEWHERE DURING THE DAY
THEY ALL WENT
BEHIND MY BACK AND SAID
WE'RE VOTING ANDREA.
IT IS REALLY HARD TO BE LIVING
WITH THESE PEOPLE FOR 32 DAYS
AND HAVE THESE RELATIONSHIPS
AND WHAT YOU THINK IS TRUST
AND FIND OUT
THAT THEY'VE BEEN LYING
TO YOU THE ENTIRE TIME.