>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AT OMETEPE, MATT AND
ANDREA FORMED A TIGHT BOND RIGHT
FROM THE START.
AND BOSTON ROB SAW THEM AS A
THREAT.
>> I KNOW HOW STRONG A PAIR CAN
BE IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: SO HE SENT MATT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND, BUT MATT
REFUSED TO GO AWAY, DEFEATING
EVERYONE HE FACED, WAITING FOR
HIS SHOT TO RE-ENTER THE GAME.
FOR THE FIFTH TIME, MATT STAYS
ALIVE.
UNDER ROB'S LEADERSHIP, THE
OMETEPE TRIBE WAS FLYING HIGH
EVEN AS OLD NEMESIS PHILLIP WAS
BEGINNING TO FEEL LIKE PART OF
THE TEAM.
>> RIGHT NOW I'M ON TOP OF THE
EARTH.
>> Jeff: AND ROB HAD ANOTHER
ACE UP HIS SLEEVE.
>> IT'S A CLUE WRAPPED UP LIKE A
COOKIE BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT IT SAYS
BECAUSE I HAVE THE IDOL
SO I WILL JUST THROW IT AWAY.
>> Jeff: ON THE ZAPATERA TRIBE,
RALPH ALSO HAD A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> AWESOME!
>> Jeff: BUT HIS TRIBE WAS IN
TROUBLE.
AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE...
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
OMETEPE OPENING UP A BIG LEAD
RIGHT NOW.
EVERYBODY THROUGH THE WALL.
GRANT DOES IT!
OMETEPE BEAT ZAPATERA FOR THE
THIRD TIME IN A ROW.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, IT CAME DOWN
TO SARITA, WHO WAS LOYAL,
OR DAVID, WHO WAS BETTER AT
CHALLENGES.
SARITA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
WITH SARITA OFF TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND, THE ZAPATERA FIVE ARE
HOPING FOR A LITTLE REDEMPTION
OF THEIR OWN.
>> YEAH.
>> WE SURE BLINDSIDED HER.
>> TONIGHT, WE VOTED SARITA OFF
BECAUSE WE FELT LIKE SARITA WAS
THE WEAKEST LINK WHEN IT CAME TO
HELPING US WIN THE CHALLENGES.
>> YEAH.
I WAS GOING
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT IT.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I UNDERSTAND.
>> WE ARE DWINDLING.
WE'RE DOWN TO FIVE NOW AND WE
HAVE TO WIN THE NEXT CHALLENGE--
WE HAVE TO WIN THE NEXT TWO
CHALLENGES.
>> WE HAVE TO EVEN THIS THING
OUT.
NO ONE LIKES A LANDSLIDE.
>> WE'VE GOTTA WIN.
>> DO BATTLE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> HELLO?
MATT?
>> HEY.
>> IT'S SARITA.
>> HEY, SARITA.
( LAUGHS )
SARITA FROM THE ZAPATERA TRIBE
ARRIVED AT MI CASA ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND THIS EVENING.
I WAS QUITE HAPPY TO SEE HER
BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T APPEAR TO BE
TOO INCREDIBLY TOUGH.
YEAH, I'VE JUST BEEN HEARING
HORROR STORIES FROM ZAPATERA.
LIKE, WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON?
>> IT'S REALLY NOT THAT BAD.
THERE ARE A LOT OF AMAZING
PEOPLE.
JULIE, MIKE, STEVE, RALPH--
GOOD PEOPLE.
I LOVE THAT I CAN SHARE THE GOOD
PARTS OF ZAPATERA WITH HIM,
LIKE, HEY, HERE'S WHO YOU WANT
TO STICK WITH.
HERE WHO I'M NOT SURE ABOUT.
I LOVE BEING ABLE TO GIVE THAT
TO HIM BECAUSE HE IS A REALLY
GOOD KID.
YOU SHOULD BE A LITTLE BIT OPEN
TO MIKE.
HE'S DEFINITELY MY FAVORITE
PLAYER.
>> I'M SORT OF THINKING THAT
SARITA MIGHT BE THE LAST OF THE
DUELERS BEFORE THE MERGE.
I TRUST THE INFORMATION THAT
SHE'S BEEN GIVING ME ABOUT THE
ZAPATERA TRIBE.
>> HE'S SO EX-MARINE.
HE'S A TOTAL BAD ASS.
>> UP UNTIL THIS POINT, I WAS
SAYING IT WOULD BE BETTER FOR ME
TO HOP BACK ON THE TRAIN WITH
OMETEPE, BUT IF ALL GOES AS
PLANNED AND I CAN WIN THE DUEL,
IT WOULD BE QUITE THE OPPORTUNE
MOMENT TO STRIKE AND TAKE OUT
THE OMETEPE TRIBE.
>> I HAVE MAIL.
>> WHOOO!
>> "ANOTHER DUEL TO BE PLAYED
THIS MORNING AND YOU KNOW IT'S
ANYONE'S GAME.
THIS TIME YOUR WHOLE TRIBE WILL
WIN THIS AS ANOTHER BUFF GOES IN
THE FLAMES."
>> I WONDER IF IT'S THE LAST
ONE.
>> MERGE.
>> MAY BE, MAN.
>> COULD BE.
>> TODAY WE GOT TREE MAIL THAT
INDICATED THAT WE ARE GOING TO
SEE A DUEL AT REDEMPTION ISLAND
WITH BOTH TRIBES FULLY PRESENT.
SO WE SUSPECT THERE'S GOING TO
BE A MERGE.
>> WE SHOULD PROBABLY BRING OUR
STUFF JUST IN CASE.
>> I AGREE.
>> IF THERE'S A MERGE, WE'RE
PROBABLY GOING TO THEIR BEACH.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> IT WOULD BE FOOLISH TO LEAVE
OUR STUFF HERE.
>> MY GUT IS THEY'D COME HERE.
>> YOU'RE A GAMBLING MAN.
>> I'M A GAMBLING MAN.
>> OKAY.
THEN WHAT DO WE WANT TO RISK?
GOING TO THE OTHER BEACH AND
LOSING EVERYTHING?
BETTER TO BE SAFE THAN SORRY.
>> I KIND OF WENT THROUGH, YOU
KNOW, I'M SICK AND TIRED OF
BEING THE REDHEADED STEPCHILD!
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT, FRANKLY?
I'VE LEARNED A LOT PLAYING THE
GAME WITH ROB.
SO THIS IS A WHOLE NEW GAME NOW.
WE'VE GOT THE NUMBERS.
AND IF IT IS A MERGE, I'M VERY
COMFORTABLE STAYING WITH THE
OMETEPE TRIBE.
>> WOW, WE'RE ALL GOING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MIGHT
MEAN?
A DUEL FOLLOWED BY A MERGE.
>> WOULDN'T THAT BE CRAZY?
>> MY PERSONAL HOPE IS WE GET TO
A MERGE, I'M READY TO SINK MY
TEETH IN TO SOME OF THE OTHER
MEMBERS OF THE OMETEPE TRIBE.
ROB IS THE OBVIOUS TARGET.
HE'S A MASTER AT THIS GAME.
I'M READY TO GET IN THE RING AND
GO TOE TO TOE WITH THAT GUY.
>> TODAY IS DUEL NUMBER 6
FOR ME.
I'M REALLY NERVOUS BECAUSE I CUT
MY FOOT PRETTY BADLY.
IT'S RIGHT ON THE OUTSIDE OF MY
FOOT SO IF IT'S ONE OF THOSE
ENDURANCE CHALLENGES IT'S GOING
TO BE REALLY, REALLY DIFFICULT.
BUT GOD GAVE ME THIS PLATFORM
AND I'M GOING TO DO THE BEST I
CAN AND HOPEFULLY COME OUT WITH
ANOTHER VICTORY.
>> MATT IS GOING TO BE HARD TO
BEAT BUT I AM GOING IN WITH SO
MUCH CONFIDENCE.
I THINK I'M A WORTHY OPPONENT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
MATT WILL BE BATTLING AGAINST
SARITA.
VOTED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
WE'VE INVITED EVERYBODY FROM
BOTH TRIBES TO WITNESS YOUR DUEL
TODAY.
BECAUSE THE WINNER OF TODAY'S
DUEL WILL GO BACK IN THE GAME.
>> IF MATT WINS, IT'S NO GOOD
FOR ME PERSONALLY BECAUSE YOU
KNOW, I'M ONE WHO SENT HIM TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
SO I'M FIGURING HE'S HOLDING
THAT AGAINST ME.
AND THERE'S A POSSIBILITY HE
MIGHT DEFECT TO THE OTHER TEAM.
I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT I WOULD DO.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU
WILL USE YOUR ARMS TO BRACE
YOURSELF AGAINST TWO WALLS WHILE
YOUR BARE FEET ARE PERCHED ON
VERY NARROW FOOTHOLDS.
EVERY 15 MINUTES, YOU'LL MOVE TO
A SMALLER FOOTHOLD.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
THIS DUEL, RE-ENTERS THE GAME,
AND CONTINUES THEIR QUEST FOR
THE MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD.
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT.
IT'S A BIGGIE.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ALL RIGHT, THIS DUEL IS ON.
YOU'LL STAY ON THIS FOOTHOLD FOR
15 MINUTES.
IF YOU'RE STILL GOING, THEN
WE'LL MOVE TO THE NEXT SMALLER
FOOTHOLD.
>> ZEN, SARITA.
>> PIECE OF CAKE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU'VE
BEEN UP THERE 15 MINUTES.
IT IS TIME TO MOVE DOWN TO THE
NEXT FOOTHOLD.
YOU'VE GOT 15 SECONDS...
GET SITUATED....
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
THE CHALLENGE CONTINUES.
>> ALL RIGHT, MATT.
>> Jeff: YOU'LL BE ON THIS
FOOTHOLD FOR 15 MINUTES.
NOW YOU'RE PROBABLY DOWN TO
ABOUT A QUARTER INCH OF WOOD
THAT YOUR FEET ARE RESTING ON.
IT'S GOING TO BE A LITTLE MORE
PAINFUL.
PHILLIP, GIVE US SOME INSIGHT.
THE SITUATION LIKE THIS, WHAT DO
DO YOU TO BE SUCCESSFUL?
>> WELL, THE BUSCHUTO CODE WAS
HOW A SAMURAI KNEW HE HAD TO
CONDUCT HIS LIFE WHEN HE WAS
FACING DIFFICULT CIRCUMSTANCES,
AND THEY HAD A WHOLE STRATEGY
ABOUT THE TASK AT HAND, AND THEY
SHAMED THEIR FEUDAL LORD, THEY
WOULD HAVE TO CUT THEMSELVES.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE THINGS THEY
LOOKED FOR, AND THEY LOOKED FOR
YOU TO MAKE THE FIRST MOVE, AND
THEN THEY WOULD STRIKE.
AND THE BUSCHUTO CODE GAVE
THEM A WAY TO LIVE AS THE BIBLE.
FOR MATT, IT'S GIVEN HIM
A WAY TO LIVE.
I KNOW HE KNOWS IT'S ALL UP
HERE.
AND AS LONG AS HE KEEPS THAT
FOCUS, HE'LL BE JUST FINE.
>> THANKS, PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: IT IS TIME NOW TO
MOVE TO THE THIRD AND FINAL
FOOTHOLD.
YOU'LL HAVE 15 SECONDS,
GET SETTLED.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE REALLY LOCKED
IN BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO BE
STUCK HERE TILL THE END OF THE
CHALLENGE.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
GOOD WORK, SARITA.
>> GOOD JOB, SARITA.
ZEN, BABY.
>> Jeff:YOU ARE NOW ON THE
FINAL FOOTHOLD.
THERE IS NO TIME LIMIT NOW.
WE GO UNTIL ONE OF YOU DROPS.
THIS IS IT.
YOU'RE ON PROBABLY AN EIGHT OF
AN INCH OF WOOD RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S VERY LITTLE THERE.
>> GOOD JOB, SARITA.
STAY THERE.
>> YOU OWN THIS, SARITA.
YOU OWN THIS.
>> Jeff: WOMEN HAVE DONE VERY
WELL IN THIS CHALLENGE,
HISTORICALLY.
>> LOOKING GOOD, MATT.
>> Jeff: MATT READJUSTING A
LITTLE BIT.
CRAMPS PROBABLY STARTING TO SET
IN.
WORKING THEIR WAY ALL THE WAY UP
YOUR LEGS.
>> YOU GOT THIS, SARITA.
>> GOOD JOB, SARITA.
>> KEEP ON GOING.
>> GOOD JOB, GIRL.
>> Jeff: SARITA FINDING THAT
ZONE.
>> YOU'RE LOOKING GREAT, MATT.
HANG IN THERE, MAN.
YOU'RE LOOKING REAL GOOD.
>> OH, GOD.
>> Jeff: SARITA DIGGING DEEP.
KEEP DIGGING.
YOU WANT A SHOT BACK IN THIS
GAME, YOU GOT IT.
SARITA DROPS OUT OF THE DUEL.
MATT SEIZES THE MOMENT AND WILL
RE-ENTER THIS GAME.
>> GOOD JOB, SARITA.
>> GREAT, GREAT TRY, SARITA.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: HOW YOU FEELING?
>> I'M BUMMED.
I THOUGHT I HAD IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SARITA,
YOU ARE OUT OF THIS GAME.
YOUR SHOT AT THE MILLION DOLLARS
IS OVER.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
TOSS YOUR BUFF ON YOUR WAY OUT.
>> SEE YOU BACK HOME, SARITA.
>> HAVE FUN, YOU GUYS.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: MATT,
CONGRATULATIONS.
SIX DUELS, SIX WINS.
YOU ARE BACK IN THIS GAME.
YOU CAN TAKE YOUR BUFF OFF, TOO.
I'VE GOT A NEW ONE FOR YOU.
IT'S CLEAN.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> Jeff: AND IT'S A DIFFERENT
COLOR.
BECAUSE WE ARE MERGED.
>> WHOA!
( CHEERS )
>> YES!
>> Jeff: DROP YOUR OLD ONE,
PUT ON YOUR NEW ONE, AND REJOIN
THE ONE TRIBE.
ALL RIGHT, ARE YOU GOING TO
MERGE TO A NEW BEACH.
HERE'S A MAP.
ONE MORE THING-- BEGINNING WITH
THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
REDEMPTION ISLAND STARTS AGAIN.
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: THAT MEANS, MATT, YOU
COULD BE VOTED OUT AGAIN
AND SENT RIGHT BACK HERE.
>> GUYS, JUST PLEASE,
GIVE ME A MINUTE.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD OUT,
LEAVE YOUR OLD BUFFS BEHIND.
>> THIS IS-- THIS IS CRAZY.
I'M ABSOLUTELY STOKED TO BE BACK
IN THE GAME RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN, I DEFINITELY THINK MY
TIME ON REDEMPTION ISLAND GIVES
ME AN ADVANTAGE BECAUSE I HAD
SIX PEOPLE BREAK DOWN EVERYTHING
THAT WAS GOING ON IN EACH TRIBE.
NOW I'VE GOT A COUPLE OF
OPTIONS.
I CAN EITHER GO WITH OMETEPE.
I CAN GO WITH ZAPATERA.
BUT I'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL
BECAUSE ONE SLIP-UP OUT HERE AND
YOU'RE GONE.
>> YES, YES, YES!
>> WALKING UP AND SEEING ALL
THAT FOOD WAS LIKE A DREAM COME
TRUE.
MY WHOLE BODY GOT HAPPY.
I FELT LIKE JUST A LITTLE KID AT
A CARNIVAL.
( SCREAMING )
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, THANK YOU!
>> THIS IS HEAVEN.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WE SAT DOWN.
WE HAD A GREAT PICNIC, FINALLY
GOT SOME GOOD FOOD.
WE HAD PRUSCIUTTO, BREAD,
WINE, LOCAL BEER,
BIG DEAL OF MIXED NUTS, DATES.
WE'VE GOT CHICKEN TO COOK
TONIGHT.
LIFE'S PRETTY GOOD RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU GUYS WHAT, DO YOU THINK
OF A NAME?
>> WHO'S GOT SOME SPANISH NAMES.
>> MURLONIO MEANS
"FROM THE SEA UNITED."
>> OH, MY GOSH, THAT'S
BEAUTIFUL.
>> DOES EVERYONE LIKE THAT?
>> SAY IT ONE MORE TIME?
>> MURLONIO.
MURLONIO DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
IT'S AN INSIDE JOKE BETWEEN
AMBER AND I.
SHE HAS A BUNCH OF STUFFED
ANIMALS AND MURLONIO IS THE
RINGLEADER SO THAT'S THE NAME OF
OUR NEW TRIBE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, MURLONIO!
>> FIRST THING ON MY MIND WHEN I
FOUND OUT WE HAD TO BUILD A NEW
SHELTER WAS OH, MY GOSH.
WE'VE GOT TO DO THIS AGAIN.
BUT I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
ACTUALLY THAT WE DID BUILD THE
SHELTER ALL TOGETHER BECAUSE
THAT'S THE ICEBREAKER.
>> LET'S THROW THE DECK IN.
>> MATT IS THE KEY LINCHPIN TO
THIS WHOLE DEAL.
HE WAS VOTED OUT BY THE OMETEPE
TRIBE, AND I THINK AT THIS
POINT, HE DOESN'T HAVE A HUGE
AMOUNT OF LOYALTY TOWARDS THEM.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE MATT AND
ANDREA ARE VERY TIGHT, SO THIS
IS WHERE I GOTTA GO FOR BROKE.
I GOTTA TRY AND MAKE AS BIG OF A
MOVE AS I CAN BECAUSE I DON'T
WANT TO JUST JUST SIT BACK AND
GET DEALT WITH WHEN IT'S MY TIME
AT THE HANDS OF BOSTON ROB.
>> THE WAY IT STANDS RIGHT NOW,
IF ROB GETS WHAT HE WANTS, HE'S
JUST GOING TO TAKE US OUT ONE BY
ONE, AND THEN I THINK IT'S
PROBABLY GOING TO BE YOU,
ANDREA, AND PHILLIP NEXT.
AND YOU ANDREA ARE THE BIGGEST
CHESS PIECES IN THIS GAME RIGHT
NOW AND I TRUST YOU GUYS
WHOLEHEARTEDLY.
AND, YOU KNOW, IF YOU GUYS CAN
TEAM UP WITH US, I CAN ASSURE
YOU THAT WE CAN GO TO THE FINAL
FOUR.
>> I BELIEVE YOU.
>> OKAY?
>> AND I'M OKAY WHITTLING DOWN
MY TRIBE TO HONOR MY COMMITMENT
TO YOU AND ANDREA BECAUSE YOU'RE
INTEGRAL PARTS TO THIS THING.
>> I WANT TO BE IN THIS GAME AS
LONG AS I CAN SO I'M REALLY JUST
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT'S BEST
FOR ME AND WHICH ROUTE TO TAKE
BECAUSE LAST TIME I WAS COASTING
AND WAITING TO PLAY THE GAME AND
THIS TIME I CAN'T BE NEAR AS
PASSIVE BECAUSE I'LL BE BACK ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND IN A JIFFY.
>> HERE'S THE DEAL.
IF YOU NEED THE IDOL,
YOU'VE GOT IT.
>> I LIKE THE SOUND OF IT.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I JUST GOTTA TALK THINGS
OVER WITH ANDREA.
>> IT IS TRULY IN HER BEST
INTEREST AS WELL.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> ...AND IT'S LEAKING LIKE A
SIEVE
ON THE BACK HALF WHERE
ZAPATERA IS.
>> THERE'S A DIVISION BETWEEN
US, AND IT'S PRETTY TOUGH BEING
ON THE DOWN SIDE OF A 7-5 TRIBE.
ANDREA AND MATT, I HOPE THEY'RE
READY TO SWITCH SIDES.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE DEAD.
>> WHEN YOU WERE BLINDSIDED,
I HAD NO IDEA.
>> LET ME TELL YOU THIS RIGHT
NOW.
RIGHT NOW,
YOU ARE MY CLOSEST ALLY.
>> GOOD.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
YOU WERE THINKING.
>> OKAY, THIS IS WHAT I WANT.
I WANT TO TAKE OUT THE OMETEPE
TRIBE.
BECAUSE I'M HONESTLY AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE ALLIANCE.
I WAS THINKING, LIKE, WE VOTE
STEVE OUT, AND THEN WE VOTE
PHILLIP OUT.
OMETEPE THINKS EVERYTHING IS
HUNKY DORY AND THAT'S WHEN WE
BLINDSIDE ROB.
>> OH, MY GOD!
I'M SO NERVOUS.
>> JUST STOP. JUST CALM DOWN
AND JUST HEAR ME OUT.
THIS GAME RESPECTS BIG MOVES.
>> YEAH.
>> IT DOES.
AND THIS IS A HUGE MOVE.
>> RIGHT NOW
I AM TIGHT WITH ROB--
I HAVE TO MAKE IT SEEM LIKE
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
WE CAN ONLY TALK TO EACH OTHER
ABOUT THIS.
>> WE CANNOT SAY
ANYTHING TO THEM.
I WILL CONSIDER THAT WE HAD THIS
A LONG TIME FROM NOW.
I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH CUTTING
THOSE TWO BECAUSE THEY KIND OF
BACKSTABBED US IN THE BEGINNING.
>> YEAH.
>> I REALLY LIKE MATT, BUT HE
HAD THIS IDEA THAT HE WANTED TO
BLINDSIDE THE OMETEPE TRIBE,
AND IN THE BACK OF MY MIND I'M
THINKING, THIS COULD BE BAD.
IT'S EXTREMELY RISKY FOR ME TO
JUMP SHIP AT THIS POINT.
BUT I'M DEFINITELY KEEPING MY
OPTIONS OPEN.
>> HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT ARE YOU READING OVER THERE?
>> MATTHEW, THE STORY OF JESUS'
ESCAPE TO EGYPT.
>> FORGOT ALL ABOUT THAT.
>> YEAH.
ABOUT THE SAME TIME AS
"SURVIVOR"?
>> YEAH AND THIS MAY SOUND CRAZY
TO YOU ALL, BUT AFTER I BEAT
STEPHANIE, IT WAS LIKE GOD
WANTED ME TO WIN REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
I REALLY FEEL I WAS PUT HERE FOR
A REASON, AND THAT THAT REASON
WAS, I BELIEVE, TO HONOR MY GOD.
SO I'M MORALLY CONFLICTED HERE
BECAUSE I REALLY GENUINELY CARE
ABOUT EVERYONE ON THE FORMER
OMETEPE TRIBE.
PART OF ME WANTS TO DO THE BIG
"SURVIVOR" MOVE.
HOWEVER, RIGHT NOW, I FEEL LIKE
MY HEART'S ALMOST TELLING ME NOT
TO AND JUST TO STICK WITH
OMETEPE.
>> "MAN DOES NOT LIVE ON
BREAD ALONE BUT ON EVERY WORD
THAT COMES FROM THE MOUTH OF
GOD."
THAT'S JUST SUCH BEAUTIFUL
LANGUAGE, YOU KNOW?
WHAT WOULD I REALLY SAY?
THERE'S LIKE A CHRISTIAN
COALITION BREWING HERE IN
NICARAGUA.
LOOK, I GOT NOTHING AGAINST GOD.
I MEAN, I GO TO CHURCH ON
SUNDAY, BUT ANY TIME A GROUP OF
INDIVIDUALS LIKES THE SAME
THING, I DON'T LIKE THAT.
IT COULD BE ROMANTIC COMEDIES.
IT COULD BE OREO COOKIES.
IF THEY'RE ALL LIKING IT
TOGETHER, I WANT THAT BROKEN UP.
WHO KNOWS, MIKE, MAYBE HE
ALREADY THINKS HE'S GOING TO
GRAB ONE OR TWO OF THEM.
CAN'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
IF MIKE DOESN'T WIN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY I FEEL LIKE HE SHOULD
BE THE FIRST SENT OVER THERE TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
ANDREA, I WILL TAKE BACK TRIBAL
IMMUNITY.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS DONE.
THIS IS NOW WHAT YOU COVET.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> OH!
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
IF YOU ARE WEARING THE NECKLACE,
YOU ARE SAFE IN THIS GAME.
YOU CANNOT BE VOTED OUT.
WITHOUT IT, YOU ARE MOST
DEFINITELY VULNERABLE.
SHALL WE GET TO THE CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU WILL BE PERCHED
ON A SMALL LOG WHILE BALANCING A
BALL ON A WOODEN DISK.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS, WE WILL
ADD MORE BALLS, MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT.
IF AT ANY POINT A BALL FALLS
OFF, YOU'RE OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
>> WHOA!
>> Jeff: LAST PERSON LEFT
STANDING WINS IMMUNITY AND IS
SAFE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
MAKE SENSE?
>> YEAH.
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TAKE YOUR
SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY TAKE A SPOT
UP ON YOUR LOG.
GET COMFORTABLE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TAKE BALL
NUMBER ONE.
PLACE IT ON YOUR DISK.
I'LL GIVE YOU FIVE SECONDS.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
AND RELEASE YOUR HANDS.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
PHILLIP ALREADY HAVING TROUBLE
BALANCING ON THE LOG.
EVERYBODY ELSE
LOOKING PRETTY STEADY.
PHILLIP WOBBLING.
CAN HE SAVE IT?
NICE RECOVERY BY PHILLIP.
I'M IMPRESSED.
>> I GOT RHYTHM, BABY.
>> Jeff: 15 SECONDS LEFT IN
THIS ROUND.
HANG ON FOR 15 SECONDS AND YOU
MOVE ON.
JULIE'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE ARE DOWN TO 11.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO ADD
ANOTHER BALL.
THAT MEANS YOU CAN PUT YOUR HAND
ON THE BALL ON YOUR DISK.
YOU ARE SAFE.
GRAB A SECOND BALL.
GET STEADY.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
THIS IS GOING TO GET MUCH MORE
DIFFICULT NOW.
ASHLEY OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
TAKE A STEP BACK ON THE BENCH.
WE ARE DOWN TO 10.
DAVID NOW STRUGGLING.
GOTTA GET IT BACK.
DAVID DROPS THE BALL.
DAVID IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
30 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
YOU GUYS ARE DOING GREAT.
RALPH WAVERING A LITTLE BIT.
DIG, RALPH!
YOU'VE DONE MORE DIFFICULT THAN
THIS.
>> OH, MAN!
>> Jeff: THIS ROUND IS OVER.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR BALLS.
YOU ARE SAFE.
WE'RE GOING TO ADD THE THIRD AND
FINAL BALL NOW.
THERE WILL BE NO STOPPING.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY.
HERE WE GO.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
NOW IT WILL BE VERY DIFFICULT.
THREE BALLS STANDING ON
A ROUND LOG WITH THE WIND.
NO MORE TIME LIMITS NOW.
WE GO UNTIL
ONLY ONE PERSON IS LEFT.
ANDREA WITH A GREAT RECOVERY BUT
CAN'T HANG ON.
ANDREA'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
GRANT, DON'T LOSE IT NOW.
GRANT IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO SEVEN.
MIKE HAS NOT WAVERED THIS ENTIRE
CHALLENGE.
ROB NOW STRUGGLING.
PHILLIP WITH A GREAT RECOVERY.
LIKE HE'S RIDING A WAVE!
MATT HAS ONE BALL HANGING JUST
ON THE EDGE OF HIS DISK.
MATT IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
ROB DROPS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
PHILLIP WOBBLING.
CAN HE SAVE IT?
PHILLIP IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY GET YOUR COMPOSURE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO FOUR.
MIKE, STEVE, NATALIE AND RALPH.
ONE FORMER OMETEPE.
THREE FORMER ZAPATERAS.
I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU'RE GOING A LONG TIME.
>> COME BACK HERE
( WHISTLING )
>> Jeff: RALPH... ONE BALL
HANGING ON THE EDGE.
RALPH DROPS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO THREE.
NATALIE AND STEVE NEED TO HOPE
FOR SOMETHING TO HAPPEN TO MIKE
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW, HE'S LIKE A
STATUE.
STEVE WITH THOSE BALLS HANGING
ON THE EDGE OF THE DISK.
FOCUS.
DON'T DRIFT.
STEVE IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO THE FINAL TWO.
MIKE AND NATALIE.
MIKE, NO MOVEMENT AT ALL.
NONE.
IT'S LIKE THOSE BALLS ARE GLUED
TO HIS DISK.
NATALIE HAVING TO DO SOME
BALANCING, SOME RECOVERING.
>> Jeff: THE FIRST SIGN OF
MOVEMENT FROM MIKE.
MIKE FALLS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE,
NATALIE WINS FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> Jeff: NATALIE, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
LOOK AT THAT.
GETTING A ROUND OF APPLAUSE.
>> YAY!
>> Jeff: NATALIE, SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SHOULD
BE AN INTERESTING AFTERNOON.
11 PEOPLE, TWO NEWLY MERGED
TRIBES.
CAN'T WAIT TO GET TO TRIBAL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME, AND THAT PERSON
WILL BE SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
NICE JOB.
>> THANK YOU.
( APPLAUSE )
>> WE'RE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
AND I'VE BEEN TALKING TO MATT
ABOUT FLIPPING.
BUT IF HE DECIDES TO JOIN FORCES
WITH OMETEPE TRIBE, IT COULD BE
ME GOING TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> GOOD JOB TODAY, MAMA.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, BABY.
ALL RIGHT!
>> THANK YOU.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> NATALIE WAS A CHAMP.
>> WHAT HAPPENED IS MY FEET WENT
NUMB AND THEN THEY JUST WENT
WHOOP.
THE CHALLENGE TODAY WAS QUITE A
BATTLE.
I THINK I HUNG IN THERE FOR
ABOUT 40 MINUTES.
I WAS IN THE ZONE.
I WAS FEELING IT.
I WAS LIKE I AM COMING BACK WITH
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE AROUND MY
NECK BUT IT DIDN'T COME OUT
RIGHT, SO THIS FIRST VOTE
BETWEEN THE TRIBES IS A BIG ONE,
AND I MIGHT BE ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK.
I DON'T THINK THEY'RE GOING TO
GO AFTER STEVE OR JULIE.
I DON'T THINK THEY SEE YOU GUYS
AS THREATS.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE RALPH
OR ME BECAUSE I DID WELL AT
THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE TODAY.
>> THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE TODAY.
>> ARE YOU OKAY PLAYING THE IDOL
FOR ME TO TRY TO WIPE OUT THEIR
VOTES?
>> IF WE NEED TO.
>> OKAY.
>> ROB IS GOING TO KNOW HE'S THE
SERPENT'S HEAD AND WE'RE COMING
AFTER HIM SO I THINK WE SHOULD
TAKE OUT ROB'S RIGHT-HAND MAN
AND GO GRANT.
THEY WON'T SEE THAT COMING.
THAT'S VERY SMART.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> PRETTY AWESOME, HUH?
>> I'VE GROWN SO MUCH THROUGH
THAT REDEMPTION ISLAND
EXPERIENCE.
THAT WAS A TIME WHEN I RELIED ON
GOD, AND I WAS TOUGH.
THIS ABSOLUTELY IS A GAME, BUT
MY HEART IS TELLING ME DON'T
CHANGE.
AND I WANT TO HONOR MY GOD AND
BE TRUE TO WHO I AM.
SO I'VE DECIDED I DON'T WANT TO
SWITCH.
I DON'T WANT TO FLIP.
AND I'M JUST GOING TO HAVE TO
HAVE PEACE
WITH WHATEVER HAPPENS.
I MEAN, IF IT'S GOD'S WILL,
HE'LL TAKE ME AS FAR AS HE WANTS
ME TO GO.
ROB, MIKE WAS TELLING ME, LOOK,
I HAVE AN IDOL FOR AND YOU
ANDREA.
HIM, RALPH, AND STEVE.
AND HE'S LIKE, "AND I COULD USE
YOU TO SAVE YOU WITH IT, AND
THEN IT WOULD BE YOU IN THE
FINAL FOUR."
I'M LIKE, THAT WOULD BE COOL.
I WANT TO GO AS FAR AS I CAN.
BUT I'M WITH YOU ALL.
I WANT TO CONTINUE RELATIONSHIPS
WITH OUR TRIBE.
>> THANKS, MAN.
THAT MEANS A LOT;
IT REALLY DOES.
MATT JUST TOLD ME HE WAS
THINKING ABOUT FLIPPING AND
GOING WITH ZAPATERA.
FIRST OF ALL, HE HAS THE
AUDACITY TO THINK THAT HE'S
GOING TO COME UP WITH A PLAN TO
VOTE ME OUT.
AND THEN THE STUPIDITY TO TELL
ME THAT.
IT JUST CONFIRMED HE CAN'T BE
TRUSTED.
SO BECAUSE OF THAT, I'M GIVING
HIM A ONE-WAY TICKET BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> IT WOULD BE SUCH A GREAT
PLAN.
I HAD IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
BUT MORALLY I WAS, LIKE, GOING
BACK AND FORTH.
I'M GLAD WE TALKED BECAUSE NOW I
DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
ANYTHING.
ANDREA, I CAME CLEAN, TOLD HIM
ABOUT MIKE AND EVERYTHING.
I KNOW THEY WANTED TO BRING YOU
IN, BUT I'M NOT FLIPPING.
WE'RE NOT DOING ANY OF THAT.
>> YESTERDAY, MATT AND I WERE
LIKE OKAY, WE'RE NOT TELLING
ANYBODY WHAT WE'RE PLANNING.
AND NOW HE'S, LIKE, THROWING ME
UNDER THE BUS TO ROB.
IT'S SO STUPID BECAUSE THAT
COULD HAVE SABOTAGED MY PLAN TO
GET TO, LIKE, THE FINAL THREE
COMPLETELY.
>> SO SHOULD WE VOTE FOR SOMEONE
LIKE MIKE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST LIKE YOU'RE SWINGING
FOR THE FENCES IN THE FIRST
INNING.
>> MAYBE THE SMART THING IS TO
GO FOR SOMEONE LIKE STEVE
OR JULIE.
>> I THINK STEVE.
I DON'T THINK THEY'D GIVE UP THE
IDOL FOR HIM.
>> STEVE DOESN'T DO ...
AROUND HERE, ANYWAY.
HE TOLD ME THAT HIM AND ANDREA
WERE GOING TO JOIN UP WITH THEM.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS!
>> YUP.
HE'S TRYING TO GET US AGAIN.
IT'S GOT TO BE MATTY, BRO.
>> DUDE I'M-- HE'S SUCH A GOOD
CHRISTIAN GUY.
>> WELL, HE CAN STILL BE A GOOD
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S PLAYING BOTH SIDES
STILL. HE IS.
>> I LOVE HIM,
BUT HE'S JUST TOO NICE.
HE'S DOING THE SAME THING HE DID
THE FIRST TIME AROUND.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, I'M KIND OF FEELING
OSTRACIZED HERE.
>> YEAH.
LOOKING AT MATT, I CAN SEE
PARANOIA GETTING TO HIM, WHICH
IS A BEAUTIFUL THING TO HAVE AT
THIS POINT.
SO I THINK HE KNOWS THAT HE
COULD POTENTIALLY BE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK WITH THE OMETEPE
TRIBE.
YOU AND ANDREA
NEED TO JUMP WITH US
BECAUSE YOU'LL GO MUCH
FURTHER THAN YOU WILL WITH THEM.
I GUARANTEE YOU, ROB HAS GOTTEN
GUYS IN A PECKING ORDER.
>> I KNOW, I'M SIXTH.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> SO, WHAT AM I DOING TONIGHT?
>> EVERYBODY.
>> OKAY.
>> MATTY, COME OVER HERE,
PLEASE.
>> MATT SAID HE DOESN'T
NECESSARILY KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ON, AND BOSTON ROB
SNAGGED HIM UP.
I'M GOING TO WRITE A NOTE TO
MATT.
>> MATT, COULD YOU TWIST THIS
ONE RIGHT HERE?
>> HUH?
>> COULD YOU TWIST THIS RIGHT
HERE.
COULD YOU TWIST THAT?
>> RIGHT HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> TOP THREE, HUH?
THAT'S NOT BAD.
WE'RE ALL GETTING READY TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND MIKE SLIPS ME
THIS NOTE.
THIS IS MY GOLDEN TICKET TO THE
FINAL THREE.
SO HERE I AM, AT THE CROSSROADS
BETWEEN KEEPING MY WORD AND
BREAKING MY WORD.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
WHAT ARE THE POSSIBILITIES THAT
YOU WOULD DO SOMETHING CRAZY
TONIGHT?
>> I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO AT
ALL, LIKE... BUT...
>> HE WENT ON A WALK.
>> TONIGHT'S VOTE IS MONUMENTAL.
IF THINGS GO DOWN THE WAY
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO GO DOWN,
THEN MATTY IS GOING HOME.
IF MATT AND ANDREA ARE WITH
THEM, THEN I'M GOING TO BE IN A
WORLD OF HURT.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING DOWN.
>> ROB WANTS ME TO VOTE FOR
MATT, BUT I TRUSTED ROB ONCE
BEFORE, AND I GOT ROYALLY
SCREWED OVER.
SO IT MIGHT BE THE WISEST MOVE
TO FLIP WITH MATT BECAUSE I
COULD BE NEXT TO GO.
>> IT'S IN MATT'S HANDS
AT THIS POINT.
>> ON THE OTHER HAND, MATT'S
JUST SKETCHY AND HE'S FLIGHTY,
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> Jeff:
A LOT OF PEOPLE AT TRIBAL.
RALPH, WHAT'S 12 PEOPLE LIKE,
IN ONE CAMP LIVING TOGETHER?
>> BOY, IT'S ROUGH.
IT'S LIKE TWO TEAMS STILL YET.
WE'RE SLEEPING
IN TWO LITTLE AREAS,
AND AIN'T DOING A LOT OF
TALKING.
THEY GO THEIR WAY AND WE OUR'N.
>> IT'S CRAZY WHAT'S GOING ON
OVER THERE, JEFF.
NOBODY'S SAYING ANYTHING TO EACH
OTHER.
I NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT.
>> Jeff: DAVID, IS THIS WHAT
YOU EXPECTED?
>> IT IS ODD.
WE GOT THE REALLY BAD SIDE OF
THE SHELTER LAST NIGHT.
THEY WERE UNDER THE TARP.
WE WERE UNDER THE PALM FRONDS,
AND WE WERE SOAK WET WITHIN FIVE
MINUTES OF RAIN LAST NIGHT.
>> WE WON THE TARP, FIRST OF
ALL,
SO IF WE CHOOSE TO SLEEP
UNDER THE TARP--
>> I WOULD LIKE TO ADD THE
ASTERISK--
TO WIN, THAT I DIDN'T
REALLY TRY TOO HARD.
>> Jeff: SO ZAPATERA DID THROW
A CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> JEFF, THAT'S THE DISTINCTION
BETWEEN THE TWO TRIBES.
BECAUSE--
>> OH, PLEASE! PLEASE.
>> PLEASE DON'T INTERRUPT.
I'LL BE COURTEOUS AND LET YOU
SPEAK.
DON'T INTERRUPT.
WE WOULD NEVER NOT TRY.
AND HERE'S WHAT I'D LIKE TO SAY
ABOUT THAT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: PLEASE.
>> THERE ARE SOME ON THAT TRIBE,
LIKE DECEIT.
WHICH CAN BE BEAUTIFUL
AND GLORIOUS, BUT YOU KNOW WHEN
RECEIVED OUTWARD, IT SOMETIMES
LEAVES A STENCH SO GREAT.
YOU KNOW THAT IT'S PROBABLY
CARRYING SOMETHING PARASITIC,
AND, THEREFORE, YOU DON'T WANT
TO APROACH IT.
>> Jeff: NOW, WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS LAUGHING AT?
>> THAT.
>> WHATEVER PHILLIP JUST SAID.
IT WAS FUNNY.
>> IT IS TWO DIFFERENT TRIBES,
BUT I DON'T DISLIKE THEM AS
PEOPLE.
I THINK WE'RE BOTH BEING LOYAL
TO THE TRIBES WE ORIGINATED
WITH, AND THAT'S WHAT IT COMES
DOWN TO.
>> Jeff: AND, MATT, HERE ARE
YOU, FRESH BACK FROM REDEMPTION
ISLAND, COMING INTO THIS.
>> MAN, IT WAS SO MUCH EASIER ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
JUST NOT HAVING ALL THESE PEOPLE
AROUND.
I'VE HAD SOME PRETTY WILD TRIBAL
COUNCILS SO FAR.
I'M STARTING TO KIND OF HAVE A
FUNNY FEELING ABOUT THIS PLACE.
>> Jeff: SO, MIKE, THERE ARE
SIX OMETEPE, FIVE ZAPATERA,
AND MATT.
OBVIOUSLY, HE'S A BIG VOTE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
MATT IS THE MAN IN THE MIDDLE.
YOU CAN SEE IT WEARING ON HIM,
BUT EVERYTHING'S GOING TO FALL
OUT HERE AT THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL
AND WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUT
WHERE EVERYBODY STANDS.
>> Jeff: RALPH, WHAT DO YOU DO
TO TRY TO CONVINCE MATT TO COME
WITH YOU GUYS?
>> BE GOOD TO HIM.
TAKE HIM FURTHER IN THE GAME.
THEY DONE CANNED HIM ONCE,
SO THEY'LL PROBABLY DO IT AGAIN.
>> Jeff: MATT, FAIR ARGUMENT.
THESE ARE THE GUYS
THAT VOTED YOU OUT.
WHY GO BACK TO THEM?
>> IT'S AN EXTREMELY FAIR
ARGUMENT TO SAY THAT BECAUSE
I'VE BEEN GONE
THE PAST 15 DAYS.
IT'S NOT LIKE TIME STOPPED.
THEY CONTINUED TO GROW IN THEIR
RELATIONSHIPS AND GET CLOSER
TOGETHER.
IT LOOKS LIKE I'M ON THE BOTTOM
OF THE ALLIANCE HERE, AND
HONESTLY, I STILL EVEN STRUGGLED
TODAY WITH WHAT TO DO
BUT I'M STARTING TO SEE
THE WHOLE PICTURE.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE
A BIG VOTE
AND, MATT, YOU ARE
SMACK DAB IN THE MIDDLE OF IT.
NATALIE HAS THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE,
CANNOT VOTE FOR NATALIE.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
NATALIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY
HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> I WANT TO PLAY THIS ON MIKE.
>> Jeff: OKAY, GIVING THIS TO
MIKE.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST MIKE WILL
NOT COUNT.
ONCE THE VOTE ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, GRANT.
GRANT.
TWO VOTES GRANT.
THAT'S THREE VOTES GRANT.
FOUR VOTES FOR GRANT.
FIVE VOTES FOR GRANT.
STEVE.
FIVE VOTES FOR GRANT, ONE VOTE
FOR STEVE.
MATT.
TWO VOTES MATT.
THREE VOTES MATT.
MATT.
FOUR VOTES MATT.
WE'RE TIED.
FIVE VOTES GRANT, FIVE VOTES
MATT, ONE VOTE STEVE.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR REDEMPTION ISLAND"--
MATT.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: MATT, ONCE AGAIN,
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
YOU'RE GOING TO HEAD BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND WHERE ONCE
AGAIN YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO
GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
>> WHAT THE HELL, GUYS.
>> Jeff: WELL, THAT IS A
"SURVIVOR" FIRST.
HERE'S THE PROBLEM-- MATT IS NOW
HEADING TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
WHERE AT LEAST ONE OF THE 11 OF
YOU WILL HAVE TO FACE HIM IN A
DUEL, AND I HAVE A FEELING
FORGIVENESS, NOT GOING TO BE ON
HIS MIND.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": >> GRANT!
>> Jeff: AND ROB ARE THROUGH.
HELLO!
ROB CEMENTS
CONTROL OF HIS TRIBE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, OMETEPE!
>> Jeff: OR DOES HE?
>> I'M MY OWN MAN.
I MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS.
AND PHILLIP GETS A MAKEOVER.
PHILLIP, DID YOU HAVE A
COLLISION WITH A HAWK?
>> I ASKED FOR A SIGN,
AND OUT OF THIN AIR,
APPEARED THIS FEATHER.
>> WHAT ACTUALLY HAPPENED?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I PUT MY TRUST IN GOD AND TODAY
GOD'S WILL WAS CONTRADICTORY
TO WHAT I WANTED.
I LIKE THESE PEOPLE.
I WANT TO BE FRIENDS WITH THESE
PEOPLE.
BUT THEY DON'T WANT TO BE
FRIENDS WITH ME.
AND, APPARENTLY, I'M JUST NOT
VERY GOOD AT THIS GAME OF
"SURVIVOR."
( SIGHS )