>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": BY DAY 10,
THE TWO BIG DOGS,
RUSSELL HANTZ AND
BOSTON ROB, WERE RUNNING IN
OPPOSITE DIRECTIONS.
ROB FOUND A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
>> DING, DING.
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
THIS IS NOT A PHONY BALONEY.
>> Jeff: AND EVEN THOUGH THEY
HAD LOST THREE OUT OF FOUR
CHALLENGES, HE HELD BLIND
ALIEGENCE OVER EVERYONE ON THE
OMETEPE TRIBE EXCEPT FOR
KRISTINA AND PHILLIP.
>> I NEED TO GET RID OF HIM NOW.
GOOD-BYE, ROB.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL COULD ONLY
MUSTER LOYALTY FROM TWO ON HIS
TRIBE, KRISTA AND STEPHANIE.
AND HE COULDN'T EVEN COME CLOSE
TO FINDING AN IDOL.
>> WHERE IS THE IDOL?
>> Jeff: THE REST OF THE
ZAPATERA TRIBE WAS SO DOWN ON
RUSSELL, THEY AGREED TO THROW A
CHALLENGE SO THEY COULD SEND HIM
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHERE HE
FACED MATT IN A DUEL.
MATT STAYS ALIVE!
MATT NOT ONLY DEFEATED RUSSELL,
HE REDUCED HIM TO TEARS.
SUDDENLY, RUSSELL WAS OUT
FOR GOOD.
>> THIS IS MY LAST TIME PLAYING
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL-- KRISTINA, BOTH TIMES
THAT YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN HERE TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU'VE BEEN ON
THE HOT SEAT?
ROB'S POSITION JUST KEPT GETTING
BETTER WHEN HE GOT HIS TRIBE TO
VOTE OUT HIS BIGGEST OPPOSITION.
KRISTINA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW KRISTINA HEADS TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND WHERE HE WILL FACE MATT
IN A DUEL TO SEE WHO WILL STAY
ALIVE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> THIS IS WICKED, MAN.
>> IS THE BLANKET DRY?
>> YEAH, IT WAS RIGHT AT THE
TIP.
WITHOUT THE TARP, THAT WOULD
HAVE BEEN WET.
>> TAKE AS MUCH WET CLOTHES AS
YOU CAN OFF.
>> THANK YOU, TARP.
>> TONIGHT, KRISTINA WENT HOME
AFTER A 4-3 VOTE, THREE FOR ME,
FOUR FOR HER.
NOT TOO SURPRISING.
I SUSPECTED IT.
THERE WAS A VERY CLOSE ALLIANCE
WITH ROB AND SEVERAL OTHERS IN
THE GROUP.
THEY'VE BEEN RUNNING THE SHOW
FROM THE GET-GO.
AND I'M KIND OF LIKE THE ODD MAN
OUT AROUND HERE, EVEN THOUGH I
THINK I BRING A LOT TO THIS
TRIBE, AND SOON A COUPLE OF
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO VATO WAKE UP
AND REALIZE THAT.
>> READY FOR BED?
>> CAN WE MOVE DOWN A LITTLE BIT
THAT WAY?
YOU AND I ARE GOING TO BE REALLY
GOOD BUDDIES TONIGHT.
>> YOU GOT YOUR UNDERWEAR ON?
>> I HAVE MY UNDERWEAR ON, BUT
THAT DOESN'T STOP ME, BROTHER.
>> PHILLIP LAST NIGHT STUCK HIS
LEG IN MY BACK, LIKE HIS KNEE,
INTO MY BACK.
JUST TO BE AN ASS LAST NIGHT.
>> DO YOU THINK HE'S A LITTLE
UPSET ABOUT TRIBAL COUNCIL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
TRIBAL COUNCIL IS ALWAYS A
MISERABLE NIGHT ALL AROUND.
ON TOP OF IT, PHILLIP IS BUGGING
EVERYONE, INCLUDING MYSELF.
HE'S COMPLETELY OFF HIS ROCKER,
WALKING AROUND IN THOSE PINK
PANTIES.
NOBODY TRUSTS HIM.
>> IT'S SERIOUSLY HURTING
MY EYES.
>> AS LONG AS PHILLIP IS
AGGRAVATING EVERYBODY SO MUCH IT
TAKES ALL OF THE HEAT OFF OF ME,
SO IN A WAY, MAYBE HE NEEDS TO
STAY.
>> DAY 12-- THE SPIRITS OF THE
TRIBE ARE HIGH, YOU KNOW, AS
LONG AS WE KEEP EXCELLING IN THE
CHALLENGES.
EVERYTHING IS KIND OF COMING
ALONG AS PLANNED.
>> YOU GOT A FISH!
>> THANK YOU.
>> OUR SIX IS ROCK-SOLID,
AND MY VISION WOULD BE TO TRY TO
REACH OUT TO THOSE TWO GIRLS.
THERE'S ALWAYS HOPE TO BRING
KRISTA AND STEPHANIE IN.
>> THE FISH IS OUT THERE.
>> GO FOR IT.
>> IF WE CAN SHOW THEM THAT
WE'RE A SOLID FAMILY AND THERE'S
NO BACKSTABBING AND IT'S A SAFE
PLACE TO BE--
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT'S THE
BEST-TASTING ONE.
I'M NOT KIDDING YOU.
>> I WOULD THINK THAT THEY WOULD
WANT TO HANG TIGHT WITH US GOING
INTO A MERGE.
>> GOT SOME TREE MAIL.
THE READING OF THE SCROLL.
"ANOTHER DUEL IS HAPPENING AT
THE ARENA.
OF COURSE, YOU KNOW THE SCORE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW YOU CHOOSE
THEM.
IT'S TIME TO SEND TWO MORE."
SO WHO HASN'T BEEN?
YOU TWO, ME, AND JULIE.
>> WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> WHOEVER PICKS ONE AND FOUR?
>> ONE AND FOUR OR TWO AND
THREE.
DON'T MATTER.
>> SO ONE AND FOUR.
>> GO AHEAD, YOU TWO.
>> ONE.
>> QUICK DECISION.
>> I'M JUST READY TO GO.
FOUR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YAY!
>> (LAUGHS)
>> SORRY, DIDN'T MEAN
TO HIT YOU.
>> NOW THAT RUSSELL IS GONE,
STEPHANIE AND KRISTA, THEY'RE
NOT EVEN A THREAT.
THEY CAN GO DO WHATEVER
THEY WANT.
THEY CAN TALK ABOUT WHATEVER
WE REALLY DON'T CARE.
THEY'RE-- THEY'RE JUST PAWNS IN
THIS BIG GAME.
>> SEE YOU IN A COUPLE OF HOURS.
>> HAVE FUN.
>> WE WILL.
>> THEY CAN'T DO ANY DAMAGE
TO US.
>> WHAT ALL ARE WE GOING TO TELL
THEM?
>> HEY, CAN YOU TELL ROB THAT
WE'RE RUSSELL'S GIRLS AND WE
HATE OUR TRIBE?
I'M HOPING TO SEND THE OTHER
TRIBE A MESSAGE THAT THEY HAVE
TWO GIRLS READY TO FLIP SO WE'RE
READY TO CAUSE SOME HAVOC AND
CHAOS AND CRAZINESS
AT THE MERGE!
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS
FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
MATT WILL BATTLE AGAINST
KRISTINA, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
BOTH TRIBES SENT TWO MEMBERS TO
WITNESS TODAY'S DUEL.
ROB AND GRANT FROM OMETEPE.
KRISTA AND STEPHANIE FROM
ZAPATERA.
MATT, YOU HAVE WON BOTH DUELS
YOU'VE BEEN IN.
KRISTINA, THIS IS YOUR FIRST.
IT IS A DO-OR-DIE SITUATION.
IN ORDER TO CONTINUE YOUR QUEST
FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS, YOU
HAVE TO WIN.
LOSER GOES HOME.
HERE IT IS.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL RACE TO COLLECT
PUZZLE PIECES.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THE PIECES,
YOU WILL USE THEM TO COMPLETE A
PUZZLE IN THE SHAPE OF A CUBE.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
STAYS ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD.
THIS IS IT, ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WINNER STAYS, LOSER GOES HOME.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
IT'S A VERY SIMPLE CHALLENGE.
IT'S A 3 X 3 CUBE YOU ARE TRYING
TO PUT TOGETHER.
THE PATTERN WILL BE ON THE
OUTSIDE.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET ALL THE CUBES
UP HERE, THEN YOU START WORKING
ON IT.
AS IN THE CASE OF EVERY DUEL,
THIS IS POTENTIALLY A
MILLION-DOLLAR CHALLENGE.
MATT HAS ALL HIS PIECES.
HE'S STARTING TO WORK ON THE
PUZZLE.
KRISTINA NOW HAS ALL OF HERS.
THESE PIECES ARE NOT LIGHT.
KRISTINA MAKING SOME PROGRESS
RIGHT OUT OF THE GATE.
MATT MAKING SOME PROGRESS.
MATT LOOKING GOOD FROM THIS
ANGLE.
THINKS HE MAY BE GETTING CLOSER.
VERY CLOSE BUT WRONG.
MATT STARTING OVER COMPLETELY.
ONE MOMENT KRISTINA'S ON THE
VERGE OF PASSING OUT, THE NEXT
MOMENT SHE'S KNOCKING PIECES OFF
THE PUZZLE LIKE A TRUE
GLADIATOR.
BOSTON ROB AND GRANT WATCHING.
>> YOU RASCAL.
YOU VOTED ME OUT FOR NO REASON.
I STILL DON'T KNOW WHY.
IF YOU WANT TO EXPLAIN TO ME
WHY, WHILE I'M WORKING, IT MIGHT
CALM ME DOWN OR SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: WHY DID YOU VOTE HIM
OUT, ROB?
>> DOESN'T TAKE ONE PERSON TO
VOTE SOMEONE OUT, JEFF.
YOU KNOW THAT.
>> Jeff: KRISTINA STARTING
AGAIN NOW.
GOT SOME NEW ENERGY, LIKE MAYBE
SHE HAS A NEW IDEA.
>> IT GOES ON TOP.
>> Jeff: MATT JUST CLUED
INTO SOMETHING THAT SEEMS TO BE
HELPING HIM.
KRISTINA NOT GIVING UP.
USING EVERY BIT OF ENERGY
SHE HAS.
AND MATT THINKS HE MAY BE
GETTING CLOSER.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: MATT THINKS
HE HAS IT.
OUT OF NOWHERE.
MATT STAYS ALIVE!
>> I TOLD YOU.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: MATT, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'RE STILL IN THIS GAME.
A LOT GOING ON AT THE END OF
THAT CHALLENGE.
AS YOU ARE TALKING TO ROB AND
GRANT ABOUT WHY THEY VOTED YOU
OUT, DID YOU LEARN ANYTHING?
>> I MEAN, LIKE, I TOLD BOTH OF
THOSE GUYS THAT I WANTED TO GO
WITH THEM TO THE TOP THREE.
I MEAN, LIKE, I WANTED YOU TWO
GUYS, MAN.
SO HOPEFULLY I'LL HOP BACK UP ON
THE OMETEPE TRIBE.
>> I KIND OF LIKE THAT HE SAYS
HE WOULD STICK TO HIS TRIBE.
I WISH I FELT THE SAME HE DID.
THERE'S STILL A CLEAR DIVISION.
>> Jeff: IN YOUR TRIBE?
>> IN OUR TRIBE.
US TWO TOGETHER ON THE BOTTOM.
>> THEY MAY THINK THEY HAVE THE
NUMBERS, BUT I THINK YELLOW
MIGHT LOOK GOOD ON ME.
>> ME, TOO.
>> Jeff: WOW.
ROB, GRANT, THAT NEVER HURTS TO
HAVE TWO PEOPLE SAY, "LISTEN, WE
MIGHT BE WILLING TO MERGE WITH
YOU."
>> DOESN'T HURT IF THEY'RE
TELLING THE TRUTH.
>> I'M TELLING THE TRUTH.
>> Jeff: KRISTINA...
YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
YOUR SHOT AT REDEMPTION IS OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
PUT YOUR BUFF IN THE URN ON YOUR
WAY OUT.
>> DO I HAVE TO?
>> Jeff: YOU GOT TO.
MATT, FOR THE THIRD TIME, YOU
HAVE SEIZED THE MOMENT, AND YOUR
QUEST FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS
AND A CHANCE TO GET EVEN OR
REJOIN CONTINUES.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
AND AWAIT YOUR NEXT OPPONENT.
YOU GUYS CAN HEAD OUT.
>> I DIDN'T EVEN PLANT A SEED IN
ROB'S HEAD.
IT'S MORE LIKE I TOOK A SEQUOIA
TREE AND PUT IT IN HIS BRAIN.
THIS IS THE ONLY THING I HAVE TO
HOLD ON TO TO STAY IN THIS GAME.
>> I HATE RICE.
>> I REALLY DON'T EAT RICE
AT HOME OR ANYTHING.
IT'S LIKE 90 SECONDS TO PUT IN
THE MICROWAVE, BROWN RICE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
IT'S THE EASIEST THING EVER.
>> LIKE PEAS AND CORN AND
EVERYTHING.
I USED TO DO THAT IN COLLEGE.
>> ROB AND GRANT STEPPED AWAY TO
GO WATCH THE DUEL AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND, SO KIND OF FUNNY KIND OF
DAY FOR ME.
FOR ME, IT'S JUST, LIKE, I CAN'T
MAKE AN IMPRESSION ON THESE
LADIES SO IT'S FRUSTRATING
FOR ME.
THESE GIRLS REMIND ME OF CRABS,
TO BE HONEST, BACK AT CAMP, YOU
KNOW, PARTICULARLY NATALIE AND
ASHLEY.
I HAVE A VERY DIFFICULT TIME
TRYING TO APPROACH THEM.
THEY'RE QUICK TO MOVE AWAY.
THEY SEE ME COMING.
AND THEY DON'T WANT TO HAVE A
CONVERSATION WITH ME ABOUT IT.
THEY DEFINITELY REMIND ME OF
CRABS.
ANDREA IS A LITTLE BIT MORE
APPROACHABLE, BUT SHE'S
CAUTIOUS.
SHE DOESN'T WANT ROB OR GRANT TO
KNOW THAT SHE'S TALKING TO ME,
EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE THE ONES WHO
SENT HER CLOSEET ALLY, MATT, TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> IT'S JUST ALL WET.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
>> IT'S LOOKING GOOD.
>> BRAVO.
>> I'VE ALREADY GOT A WHOLE BED
OF THEM UNDERNEATH HERE THAT ARE
GOING TO IGNITE.
IT'S GOING TO SETTLE AND THEN
START THAT TO BURN AS WELL.
>> THAT WAS THE TICKET.
>> WE MISS THE BOYS.
LIKE, ROB AND GRANT ARE LIKE OUR
BIG BROTHERS.
LIKE, IT'S WEIRD NOT HAVING THEM
AROUND, AND SO WE HAD TO FAKE IT
TO MAKE PHILLIP FEEL PART OF THE
GROUP.
WE HAD TO FAKE IT SO ANDREA
FEELS COMFORTABLE.
THERE'S A LOT OF FAKING GOING
ON, BUT THAT'S THE NAME OF THE
GAME.
>> THE SUN'S COMING OUT, GIRLS.
ALMOST TIME FOR OUR BEACH DAY.
>> MY RELATIONSHIP WITH THE
GIRLS IS-- IS JUST-- THERE IS A
LEVEL OF FRUSTRATION THAT'S
GROWING A LITTLE BIT BECAUSE
THEY-- THEY JUST DON'T
DO THAT MUCH.
>> OH, MY GOSH,
THAT FEELS SO GOOD.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S A LITTLE AGITATING TO ME
BECAUSE I WANT TO KEEP, YOU
KNOW, GETTING STUFF DONE AND
KEEP GOING BUT I ALSO KIND OF
HAVE TO
HANG OUT WITH THEM BECAUSE
I FEEL LIKE
US THREE GIRLS ARE TOGETHER.
THEY'RE SWEET GIRLS BUT THE
CONVERSATIONS USUALLY GOING TO
SUPERFICIAL STUFF LIKE, "OH,
HOW'S MY HAIR," TALKING ABOUT
STUFF LIKE THAT.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR BACK?
WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT'S ME PICKING MY SKIN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
STOP.
>> IT ONLY LOOKS BAD RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE IT'S, LIKE, WET.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> THAT'S MY HABIT.
>> WHAT'S UP, GIRLS?
>> RIGHT NOW, EVERYONE FEELS
SAFE AND OH, WE HAVE OUR FIVE,
WE HAVE OUR FIVE.
BUT I MEAN, IF I HAD IT MY WAY I
WOULD WANT TO GET RID OF NATALIE
AND ASHLEY BEFORE PHILLIP BUT I
CAN'T REALLY BRING THAT UP
WITHOUT PUTTING MYSELF ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> YOU WENT TO THEM.
YOU GOT A GOOD SHOT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I LIKE YOU A LOT.
I THINK YOU'RE THE BEST FEMALE
WORKER HERE.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
LIKE, IT'S A LITTLE FRUSTRATING
TO BE HERE WHEN THERE'S, LIKE
STUFF ALWAYS TO BE DONE.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU STILL HAVE TO PLAY THE
SOCIAL GAME SO YOU CAN'T JUST
BE DOING WORK THE ENTIRE TIME.
YOU HAVE TO SOCIALIZE, TOO.
>> LOOK AT ME.
I'M STUCK.
I MEAN, I FEEL FRUSTRATED IN
THIS GAME BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
CONNECTED WITH ANY OF YOU, THE
YOUNGER LADIES.
YOU'VE, I'VE COME A TINY BIT
HAVING CONVERSATIONS WITH, BUT
THE OTHER TWO, THEY CAN'T ENGAGE
ME.
>> I CAN ASK YOU SOMETHING?
>> YEAH.
>> HONESTLY?
>> THERE HASN'T BEEN ANY POINT
IN THIS GAME WHATSOEVER THAT YOU
TRIED TO THROW ME UNDER THE BUS
OR DO ANYTHING AGAINST ME.
>> NEVER?
>> NEVER.
>> OKAY.
I WASN'T, LIKE SUSPICIOUS.
BUT IT'S HARD TO TRUST ANYONE
OUT HERE.
>> ONLY ROB AND GRANT-- YOU GUYS
ARE PULLING ALL THE STRINGS.
I SLEEP BY MYSELF.
NOBODY CUDDLES UP WITH ME AND
HAVE THAT LITTLE CHAT, CHAT,
CHAT, RIGHT?
>> LITTLE WHAT?
CHAT, CHAT, CHAT, CHAT?
>> WHATEVER YOU GUYS TALK ABOUT.
I'M SURE YOU AND MATT--
>> MATT'S LONG GONE.
>> I KNOW, BUT AT ONE POINT YOU
TALKED ABOUT THE GAME, THE
STRATEGY, WHATEVER.
I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE TO DO THAT
WITH ANYONE HERE.
IF MATT COMES BACK-- I'M GOING
TO PUT THIS OUT TO YOU-- YOU,
ME, AND MATT BEING AN ALLIANCE.
I DON'T LIKE ROB BACKSTABBING
MATT.
AND I'M JUST
WAITING FOR MY TIME.
AND THAT'S WHAT'S
FRUSTRATING FOR ME.
THEY DON'T REALIZE
THIS GUY HAS A HISTORY OF
THROWING PEOPLE UNDER THE BUS
WHEN IT SUITS HIS NEEDS.
I MEAN, SOME REAL SYNERGY WITH
ANDREA TODAY.
AND I THINK THAT MAYBE IN THE
FUTURE, THAT WILL HOLD SOMETHING
BOTH FOR SHE AS WELL AS FOR I.
>> WELL?
>> KRISTINA WON!
>> NO!
>> NO, I'M JUST KIDDING.
>> OH, MY GOSH, DON'T DO THAT!
>> TO FULLY UNDERSTAND MY
RELATIONSHIP WITH ROB IS THE
KING IS A DICTATOR, AND I'M A
LORD, AND I'M WAITING FOR MY
OPPORTUNITY TO REPLACE THE KING.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK.
>> I DON'T, EITHER.
THAT WAS LIKE HEAVEN.
>> REDEMPTION ISLAND IS
BEAUTIFUL BECAUSE WE GOT TO
SPEAK AND ROB HEARD US LOUD AND
CLEAR UNLESS FOR SOME REASON HE
LOST HIS HEARING BECAUSE AS HE
WAS LEAVING, HE TOLD US TO HANG
ON.
AND THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
DO.
WE'RE GONNA HANG ON.
>> WHAT ALL ARE WE GOING TO
TELL THEM?
>> I SAY EVERYTHING THAT WE CAN
TELL THEM EXCEPT THE POINT WHERE
WE OFFERED ROB OUR TWO VOTES.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I THINK ROB KIND OF FEELS
LIKE HIS HEAD IS ON THE LINE
HERE BECAUSE OUR TEAM GOT RID OF
RUSSELL SO QUICKLY, YOU KNOW,
FOR NO REASON.
>> I KNOW.
>> I MEAN, THEY HAVE TO NOTICE
THE DIVISION.
SO, BASICALLY, IF WE KEEP
WINNING HE'LL KNOW ADD TWO, ADD
TWO, ROB.
WHATEVER YOU THINK YOUR NUMBERS
ARE RIGHT NOW YOU BETTER ADD TWO
BECAUSE WE ARE TOTALLY WITH YOU.
OKAY, I'M A LITTLE EXCITED.
TAKE IT DAY BY DAY, DAY BY DAY.
WE JUST NEED TO KEEP WINNING THE
CHALLENGES.
>> YEAH. OKAY.
>> THIS IS OUR BEST THING RIGHT
NOW AND HOPEFULLY THINGS GO OUR
WAY.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING I CAN HOLD
ON TO RIGHT NOW BECAUSE MY HEAD
IS ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK AND I
DON'T WANT MY HEAD TO GO
A-ROLLING.
>> PUT THE TEAM ABOVE YOURSELF,
YOU KNOW, OUT HERE.
EVERY TEAM THING I EVER PLAYED
WAS ALWAYS A SUCCESS.
LIKE THEY SAY, THERE'S NO "I"
IN TEAM.
>> SINCE RUSSELL HAS LEFT, THERE
HAS BEEN ZERO TALK OF STRATEGY.
>> IT'S GOT TO BE GETTING UGLY
AT THE OTHER CAMP.
>> IT'S GOT TO BE REALLY UGLY.
>> ONE MORE DEFEAT WILL BE A
BACKBREAKER.
>> EVERYTHING HAS BEEN, "HOW
AWESOME WE DID AT THE
CHALLENGE."
"NO, IT WAS YOU."
THAT'S ALL THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
THEY DON'T PLAY THE GAME AND
WHEN THE GAME MAKES THEM PLAY
IT, THEY'RE GOING TO BE VERY
DISAPPOINTED.
>> WOULD YOU LIKE FRESH
TORTILLAS TODAY, SIR?
>> TO AVOID HANGING OUT
WITH THE TRIBE, EXCLUDE YOURSELF
BY MAKING THE MEAL.
THEN YOU WON'T HAVE TO PUT UP
WITH THE BORING STORIES YOU'VE
ALREADY HEARD 95 TIMES.
>> KRISTA AND STEPHANIE, THEY'RE
KIND OF ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF OUR
TRIBE.
>> ANYBODY HAVE
ANY WATER TO SPARE?
>> I KNOW THAT THEY'RE
DEFINITELY CONSPIRING TOGETHER.
I MEAN, THEY WERE PART OF
RUSSELL'S ALLIANCE, AND THEY'VE
REMAINED PRETTY TIGHT FROM
THERE.
SO THERE DEFINITELY ARE SOME
RISKS, BUT I DON'T SEE IT
PLAYING INTO THE GAME TOO MUCH
AT THIS POINT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO GO HARD.
>> HARD, GUYS.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> THERE'S ONLY VICTORY TODAY,
GUYS.
>> YUP.
>> ONLY VICTORY.
>> ONE CHOICE.
>> WELL, I'M BACK, MAN.
MY STRENGTH IS BACK.
>> THE HEAD BAND
GOES ON, GAME TIME.
WE'VE GOT TO WIN TODAY.
>> I FEEL LIKE THE TRIBE IS A
LITTLE OVER-CONFIDENT
RIGHT NOW,
AND THERE'S REASON FOR IT, BUT
WE THREW THAT CHALLENGE, AND I
HOPE IT DOESN'T COME BACK TO
BITE US.
YOU KNOW, ONCE YOU START
WINNING YOU GET ON A ROLL, AND
TO STOP THAT ROLL, I'M A LITTLE
SUPERSTITIOUS WHEN IT COMES TO
THAT SO I WANTY EVERYBODY TO
KEEP THINGS IN CHECK, YOU KNOW,
UNTIL WE ACTUALLY WIN,
THEN WE CAN
BE COCKY OR WHATEVER, BUT RIGHT
NOW, IT'S KIND OF BAD KARMA.
>> STEAM, STEAM, STEAM, STEAM!
>> YOU JUST PUT THE FIRE OUT!
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
GIVE IT UP, DAVID.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ONE
PERSON ON EACH TRIBE WILL BE
YOUR CALLER.
THE OTHER TRIBEMATES WILL BE
BLINDFOLDED.
USING ONLY VERBAL COMMANDS, THE
CALLER MUST GUIDE THEIR
TRIBEMATES THROUGH A MAZE TO
COLLECT BAGS OF PUZZLE PIECES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL FOUR,
THE CALLER WILL THEN USE THOSE
PIECES TO SOLVE A WORD PHRASE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION,
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR A REWARD.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING YOU NEED
TO MAKE COFFEE-- SUGAR, CREAM,
AND HONEY.
AND, CLEARLY, YOU HAVE A
BASKETFUL OF PASTRIES.
>> I COULD EAT THE BASKET.
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA, YOU HAVE
TWO EXTRA MEMBERS, SITTING TWO
PEOPLE OUT THIS CHALLENGE.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
STEVE AND JULIE GOING TO SIT
THIS ONE OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> WHO'S CALLING?
WHO'S CALLING?
>> I'M CALLING.
>> IF YOU ARE CALLING OUT THE
DIRECTIONS, YOU ARE ALSO BEING
THE PUZZLE MAKER AND STEPHANIE
IS GOOD.
SHE IS A LINGUIST, YOU CAN TELL.
I KNEW SHE WAS GOING TO BE GREAT
AT CALLING THINGS OUT.
SHE'S BOSSY AS ALL GET-OUT, SO
THAT WAS DEFINITELY THE JOB
FOR HER.
>> WAIT.
>> GO THROUGH THE PUZZLE
SEQUENCE AGAIN.
>> THREE, FIVE, FIVE, TWO,
SEVEN.
>> LOOK FOR THE FIRST WORD TO BE
"THE."
I'M NOT GOD GIFT'S TO THE PUZZLE
WORLD BUT I'M MORE QUALIFIED TO
BE DOING A WORD PUZZLE THAN
STEPHANIE.
SERITA IS TRYING TO BE TOO FAIR.
LET EVERYBODY HAVE A CHANCE,
EVERYBODY PLAY.
THIS ISN'T LIKE A PEEWEE
SOCCER LEAGUE.
>> I'M GO TO DIRECT GRANT.
EVERYBODY WILL FOLLOW HIM.
>> I'M GOOD AT PUZZLES.
>> THIS COULD BE A TURNING POINT
FOR THIS TRIBE.
THERE'S NO WAY THEY CAN TAKE
THIS WIN AWAY FROM US.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, STEPHANIE
IS THE CALLER FOR ZAPATERA.
BOSTON ROB IS THE CALLER FOR
OMETEPE.
THEY WILL ALSO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR SOLVING THE WORD PHRASE AT
THE END.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> STRAIGHT AHEAD, KEEP GOING,
STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT.
>> STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT, KEEP
GOING.
HANG ON TO RALPH, GUYS.
>> STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT.
>> STRAIGHT.
>> GO STRAIGHT, RALPH.
>> COME ON, COME ON, GET AHOLD
OF MY HAND.
>> GRANT, GO, GO, GO.
LEFT, GRANT.
>> THE BAG IS RIGHT THERE.
UNTIE IT!
>> Jeff: MIKE HAS A BAG FOR
ZAPATERA.
>> LEFT, LEFT, LEFT, GRANT.
GRANT, LEFT.
RIGHT THERE.
THERE IT IS.
>> Jeff: GRANT HAS A BAG FOR
OMETEPE.
>> ASHLEY, GO STRAIGHT.
>> HANDS DOWN SERITA.
TO THE RIGHT.
THAT'S YOUR BAG.
>> Jeff: SERITA HAS A BAG FOR
ZAPATERA.
>> MOVE TO YOUR LEFT.
>> Jeff: KRISTA HAS A BAG FOR
ZAPATERA.
>> RIGHT THERE, GRANT,
TURN AROUND.
RIGHT THERE, THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: GRANT HAS THE FIRST
BAG ON THE TABLE FOR OMETEPE.
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY HAS A BAG.
>> STEPHANIE.
>> SERITA STOP, TURN AROUND, GO
STRAIGHT.
>> WHERE DO I NEED TO GO?
>> RALPH, WAIT.
OTHER PEOPLE.
TURN, TURN, TURN, PERFECT.
LEAVE THE BAGS IN THERE.
>> HEY, AIN'T NOTHING THERE!
>> RALPH, STOP TALKING!
>> Jeff: SERITA AND KRISTA
HAVE THE FIRST TWO BAGS FOR
ZAPATERA.
>> GO FORWARD, FORWARD.
STOP! MAKE A LEFT.
>> ASHLEY, MAKE A LEFT AND GO
STRAIGHT.
GRANT, STOP.
PUT YOUR HAND TO THE RIGHT.
>> Jeff: GRANT WITH ANOTHER BAG
FOR OMETEPE.
>> SERITA, LEAD HIM INTO THE BOX
YOU WERE JUST IN.
>> Jeff: MIKE HAS A THIRD BAG
BACK TO THEIR TABLE.
>> KEEP GOING, ASHLEY,
RIGHT THERE, PUT IT DOWN.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY HAS THE SECOND
BAG FOR OMETEPE ON THE TABLE.
>> STEPHANIE, IS THERE ANYTHING
OVER HERE?
>> STEPHANIE, WHERE DO I NEED
TO GO?
>> RALPH, STOP AND WAIT UNTIL I
ADDRESS YOU.
>> YEAH, GRANT, YOU GOT IT,
STRAIGHT THROUGH, STRAIGHT TO
THE END.
>> Jeff:
OMETEPE HAS THREE BAGS.
BOTH TRIBES HAVE ONE BAG LEFT.
>> RALPH, YOUR TURN.
ARE YOU LISTENING?
MOVE TO YOUR LEFT.
NO!
YOUR OTHER LEFT!
STRAIGHT, STOP!
STRAIGHT, GO FORWARD, RALPH.
>> FORWARDS?
>> THERE IT IS, RIGHT IN FRONT
OF YOU.
>> Jeff: GRANT HAS THE FOURTH
AND FINAL BAG FOR OMETEPE.
>> WHERE IS THE LAST BAG?
>> RALPH, RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU,
ON THAT HOOK.
GRAB THAT BAG!
OPEN IT!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA WITH THEIR
FOURTH BAG.
>> KEEP GOING, GRANT,
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: ROB CAN NOW HEAD OUT
AND START WORKING
ON THE PUZZLE.
>> STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT,
GO FORWARD.
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT HERE.
>> COME ON, ROB, COME ON, ROB!
>> PUT ON THE TABLE.
PUT IT ON THE TABLE.
>> WE'RE THERE, GO!
>> Jeff: GO, STEPHANIE.
STEPHANIE NOW WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE FOR ZAPATERA.
>> COME ON, ROB!
>> Jeff: A HUGE TIME ADVANTAGE
FOR OMETEPE AND ONE OF THE BEST
PUZZLE SOLVERS IN BOSTON ROB.
>> GO, STEF, YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: IT IS A SHOWDOWN,
NOW.
BOSTON ROB AND STEPHANIE.
BOTH CALLERS VOLUNTEERED FOR
THIS JOB.
BOTH FELT CONFIDENT.
>> COME ON, YOU GOT IT!
>> Jeff: STEPHANIE, OPENING
HER LAST BAG.
>> COME ON, STEF!
>> Jeff: ROB OPENING HIS LAST
BAG OF PUZZLE PIECES.
STEPHANIE'S GOT ALL OF HERS
OPEN.
STEPHANIE NOW BACK IN THE
LEAD TIME-WISE.
SHE IS NOT MESSING AROUND.
>> SHE'S GOT IT.
I'M NOT EVEN WORRIED ABOUT HER.
>> COME ON, STEPHANIE, YOU GOT
IT, YOU GOT IT.
>> OPEN 'EM UP! HUSTLE!
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HERO OR
A GOAT ROLE.
WHEN YOU PUT YOURSELF AS THE
CALLER AND PUZZLE SOLVER YOU
BETTER BE RIGHT.
IMMUNITY AND A HUGE REWARD.
STEPHANIE MADE UP A LOT OF TIME
WHEN IT CAME TO OPENING THESE
BAGS OF PIECES.
ROB JUST DISCOVERED HE'S GOT A
MISSING PIECE.
THAT WILL MAKE IT EASIER.
>> GOOD JOB, ROB.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF
EXPERIMENTING GOING ON.
SO MANY DIFFERENT WORD
POSSIBILITIES.
>> LET'S GO, BUDDY.
THERE YOU GO.
>> HE'S GOT SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: BOTH STEPHANIE AND
ROB THINK THEY HAVE A LITTLE
SOMETHING AT THE END.
IS IT THE RIGHT WORD?
>> YOU GOT IT, STEF.
>> SHUT UP.
>> Jeff: ROB THINKS HE HAS
SOMETHING GOING NOW.
>> YOU GOT IT, ROB, HERE WE GO.
>> COME ON, STEPHANIE.
>> I WISH DAVID HAD BEEN
CALLING.
I DON'T THINK SHE'S SMART ENOUGH
FOR THIS.
>> GOOD JOB, ROB.
>> COME ON, STEPHANIE.
>> Jeff: ROB MOVING SOME
PIECES AROUND AGAIN.
>> THAT'S WHY WE NEEDED DAVID.
>> Jeff: ROB THINKS HE HAS IT.
HE DOES!
OMETEPE WINS REWARD AND
IMMUNITY.
>> AWESOME, DUDE!
AWESOME!
>> YEAH!
>> SHOULD HAVE HAD YOU DO THAT
PUZZLE.
>> YEP, DAVE SHOULD HAVE BEEN
THERE.
>> Jeff: OMETEPE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE )
>> YAY!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, OMETEPE
COME GRAB YOUR REWARD.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP AND ENJOY THE
NIGHT OFF.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> OH, MY GOD, THE SMELL,
YOU GUYS!
>> LOOK AT THAT.
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
YOUR TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND WHERE THEY
WILL HAVE TO DUEL TO STAY IN
THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> WELL, EVEN THOUGH WE LOST
TODAY IN THE CHALLENGE WE REALLY
WON.
THIS IS GOING TO BE BETWEEN
KRISTA AND STEPHANIE.
THOSE TWO ARE ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK TONIGHT.
>> MMM!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> YUMMY!
>> HOW CAN YOU NOT SMILE WHEN
YOU EAT THESE?
>> THIS IS SO GOOD.
>> OH, MY GOSH, THE CHOCOLATE
DONUTS!
I CAN'T EVEN CHOOSE A FAVORITE.
LIKE, I LOVE MUFFINS.
THOSE MUFFINS, IT WAS, LIKE,
APPLE CINNAMON OR SOMETHING.
IT WAS SO GOOD.
>> YUMMY TO VICTORY!
WE GOT A WIN TODAY.
YOU GET TO SEE MY BEAUTIFUL
WHITES MORE OFTEN.
I LOVE WHAT SUGAR DOES.
YOU SEE.
>> I KNOW.
SUGAR IS NICE.
>> FOR A MASSAGE, I'D GIVE UP
HALF A DONUT.
>> OH, YEAH, PHILLIP WAS LIKE,
"I'LL TRADE A DONUT IF SOMEBODY
GIVES ME A MASSAGE."
I WAS LIKE I WOULDN'T GIVE YOU A
MASSAGE FOR A DOZEN DONUTS,
BUDDY.
>> THAT IS COFFEE!
SMELL THAT.
>> SURE ENOUGH, I PICK UP THE
COFFEE, YOU KNOW, AFTER EATING,
EVERYONE IS DISTRACTED BY THE
FOOD, I SWIRL IT AROUND A LITTLE
BIT AND GIVE IT A SMELL, AND
AS I'M SMELLING I SEE WHAT LOOKS
LIKE TO BE A LITTLE ROLL OF
PAPER.
SURE ENOUGH, ROB SAW THE SAME
THING.
HOW DO YOU DO?
YOU GOT ALL YOUR TRIBE
AROUND, LOOKING.
BUT NOBODY CAUGHT IT,
I DON'T THINK.
>> DO YOU GUYS WANT TO SAVE THE
CROISSANTS FOR TOMORROW?
>> THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
>> DOES THAT SOUND GOOD?
>> GRANT SET A BLOCK FOR ME.
I WAS GOING TO PUT IT DOWN MY
PANTS BUT IF I DO THAT,
IT'S TOO OBVIOUS
I HAVE IT ON ME.
I WAS LIKE HOW CAN I GET THIS
WHOLE THING OVER THERE SO I CAN
MAKE HIM COME BACK TO THE CAMP.
WHEN GRANT TURNED THE OTHER WAY
HE SET A PICK FOR ME AND I WENT
AROUND THE OUTSIDE.
IT WAS LIKE A WELL-CHOREOGRAPHED
FOOTBALL PLAY.
>> HAND IT TO ME.
>> I'LL BRING IT BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL HIDE THIS.
>> YUMMY.
>> AREN'T THOSE GREAT?
>> SMELL THIS, DUDE!
THIS IS THE DARKEST--
>> NOW THAT'S REAL COFFEE.
>> THAT'S REAL COFFEE, RIGHT?
>> I'M GOING TO GO SWITCH THIS
WITH THE CLUE
THAT I ALREADY HAVE.
AND GIVE 'EM THE FIRST CLUE AND
KEEP THIS ONE.
SO WE GOTTA MOVE.
TODAY'S A GOOD DAY.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
NOT ONLY DID WE WIN IMMUNITY AND
REWARD, BUT I GOT VERY LUCKY AND
HAD SOMEONE HAND ME THE CLUE TO
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND I
JUST WENT TO GO HIDE IT FOR HIM.
UNBEKNOWNST TO GRANT, I RAN TO
MY STASH AND MY ORIGINAL HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE THEY HAD
BURIED, SWAPPED THEM OUT AND PUT
THE ORIGINAL CLUE IN MY HAND IN
PLACE OF THE ONE THAT HE THINKS
THAT WE TOOK OUT OF THE COFFEE.
THAT FIRST CLUE IS SO
RIDICULOUS.
IT SAYS SOMETHING ABOUT, LIKE,
LOOKING IN THE SAND AND UNDER A
ROCK OR MAYBE IN A TREE, DIG FOR
IT, CLIMB FOR IT.
WHO KNOWS?
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'RE FINDING
ANYTHING WITH IT.
DUDE, IT DOESN'T SAY CRAP.
>> DID YOU FIND IT?
>> YEAH.
>> NO, THE IDOL.
>> HOLD ON. UM...
>> DO YOU WANT TO JUST BURY IT?
>> LET'S THINK.
THINK, THINK, THINK.
>> DO YOU WANT TO PUT IT WHERE
THE SHOVELS ARE?
DIG A HOLE WITH THE SHOVELS.
>> AND BURY IT.
>> LET'S GO.
>> WHEN GRANT FIRST CAME UP TO
ME I WASN'T SURE IF HE HAD SAW
ME IN THE OTHER WOODS SO I HAD
TO, LIKE, YOU KNOW, PRETEND LIKE
I WAS NERVOUS.
OKAY, NOBODY WILL KNOW.
>> THIS TREE RIGHT HERE.
>> THIS IS REALLY ALL FOR
NOTHING BECAUSE I ALREADY HAVE
THE IMMUNITY IDOL, BUT IT'S FUN
FOR ME.
I HAVE TO ENTERTAIN MYSELF OUT
HERE SOMEHOW.
I HAD TO HUSTLE, YOU KNOW, BUT
YOU GOTTA HUSTLE IF YOU WANT TO
MAKE A DOLLAR.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
>> THIS IS THE PUZZLE GUY,
HANDS DOWN.
I THINK SHE TRIED HER BEST
AND I COMMEND HER FOR IT.
>> SHE DID A GREAT JOB.
SHE DID A GREAT JOB.
>> THAT JUST WASN'T HER
POSITION.
>> I THINK IN HER DEFENSE
BECAUSE DAVID IS THE PUZZLE GUY,
DAVID UNDER PRESSURE IS REALLY
STRESSFUL.
>> YOU'RE FREAKING WRONG THERE.
DON'T GO THERE WITH THAT.
ME UNDER PRESSURE MAY NOT BE
THE WAY YOU--
>> I'M JUST GIVING YOU MY
OPINION.
>> LET ME SPEAK.
ME UNDER PRESSURE MAY NOT BE THE
WAY YOU WANT IT TO BE HANDLED,
I DON'T FREAK OUT.
I DO VERY WELL UNDER PRESSURE.
MY ENTIRE LIFE IS BASED ON BEING
UNDER PRESSURE.
>> I'M JUST SAYING--
>> IT JUST DOESN'T JIBE WELL
WITH YOUR PERSONALITY MAYBE.
>> I'M JUST SAYING MY
PERSPECTIVE ON HER, NORMALLY I
WOULD HAVE DEFAULTED TO YOU--
>> THE PUZZLE MATTERS,
NOT THE MAZE.
>> THEN I THINK MAYBE
IN THE FUTURE...
>> I'M THE ONE DOING PUZZLES
FROM HERE ON OUT, NO QUESTION.
>> IT'S ABSURD FOR SERITA TO GO
WITH HER DECISION THAT STEPHANIE
THINKS SHE'S THE RIGHT PERSON.
EVERYBODY KNOWS WE HAVE A VERY
STRONG ATTORNEY.
HE LIVES WITH DOING PUZZLES.
THAT'S HIS THING.
I'M MORE DISAPPOINTED IN THE
WHOLE TEAM THAN AT STEPHANIE.
FOR A COUPLE OF STRONG
PERSONALITIES NOT TO STEP UP.
>> HERE'S THE PROBLEM-- WE'RE
ONE AHEAD AT THIS POINT.
WE NEED TO STRING A COUPLE OF
VICTORIES TOGETHER.
WE NEED TO BE REALLY, REALLY
SMART ABOUT WHO WE PUT WHERE.
THIS WAS JUST A PERSONNEL
PROBLEM.
>> IT WAS.
>> THAT'S TOTALLY TRUE.
>> STEPHANIE AND KRISTA MADE
THEIR BED ON DAY ONE, LITERALLY
AND METAPHORICALLY, RIGHT NEXT
TO RUSSELL.
SO I DON'T SEE EITHER OF THEM AS
SOMEONE I CAN TRUST.
YOU KNOW, WITH STEPHANIE'S
FLOUNDERING TODAY AT THE PUZZLE,
I MIGHT PUT HER AS ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK NUMBER ONE.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU THINK STEPHANIE CAN COME
AROUND OR DO YOU THINK SHE'S
JUST KIND OF PLAYING?
>> NO, I DON'T TRUST HER ONE
BIT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP HOPES
ON STEPHANIE.
I WANT TO KEEP WORKING ON HER
BUT KRISTA I DON'T EVEN WANT TO
WASTE MY BREATH.
I DON'T LIKE HER.
I'M HOPING WE CAN STILL
REEL STEPHANIE IN.
THEY BOTH HAVE TARGETS, BUT
KRISTA HAS THE BULL'S EYE
ON HER.
>> HER AND KRISTA AND DAVID ARE
THE PEOPLE THEY JUST-- EVEN AS
MUCH AS I WANT TO TRY TO TRUST
DAVID.
>> YEAH.
>> HE IS A LAWYER AT HIS VERY
CORE.
HE IS SO OUT FOR HIMSELF.
>> IF IT WAS ENTIRELY UP TO ME,
DAVID WOULD BE GOING HOME
TONIGHT BUT STEPHANIE AND
KRISTA, THEY PLAYED THEIR HANDS
SO EARLY ON, SO NOW IT'S KIND OF
THEY ARE TWO DEAD DUCKS SITTING
ON A LAKE WAITING FOR THE
GUNSHOTS.
>> WELL, I BELIEVE
THERE IS A WILL
AND A PLAN, AND IF THAT'S FOR
ONE OF US TONIGHT, IF THERE'S
NOTHING WE CAN DO ABOUT IT, THEN
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS JUST
CONTINUE TO FIGHT ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND AND CONTINUE
TO FIGHT HERE.
BECAUSE THEY'RE
NOT PLAYING THE GAME.
SO EVENTUALLY THIS IS ALL GOING
TO COME BACK AND BITE THEM IN
THE END.
THE SAD THING IS THERE'S--
THERE'S REALLY NO SCRAMBLING FOR
STEPHANIE AND I TO DO.
IT'S EITHER ME OR STEPHANIE
GOING HOME.
THEY'RE SO LOCKED TIGHT IN THEIR
COMFORT OF "LET'S JUST GET
THROUGH THIS ONE AND THEN WE
KNOW WE'RE SAFE."
NO MORE THINKING PAST THE FACT
THAT WHAT HAPPENS IF AFTER THIS
VOTE, EVERYONE MAKES IT TO THE
MERGE?
THEY'RE NOT THINKING ABOUT THAT.
AND WHO IS GOING TO STICK AROUND
IN THE END AND WHO WOULD YOU
WANT TO BE SITTING NEXT TO WHEN
THE VOTES COME DOWN?
IF I HAD TO PUT MONEY ON IT, I
WOULD SAY THAT NONE OF THEM ARE
GOING TO MAKE IT TO THE END.
I JUST WISH I WAS GOING TO BE
AROUND TO SEE IT.
>> Jeff: KRISTA, AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, RUSSELL WAS
VOTED OUT.
YOU AND STEPHANIE WERE PRETTY
VOCAL ABOUT THE FACT THAT IT WAS
THE THREE OF YOU IN ONE
ALLIANCE.
EVERYBODY ELSE WAS IN ANOTHER
IS THAT STILL THE CASE?
>> THAT'S STILL THE CASE.
AND AFTER RUSSELL LEFT, THERE'S
REALLY BEEN NO GAME PLAYING.
IT KIND OF SEEMS LIKE THE BRADY
BUNCH HAS GONE CAMPING AND
THEY'VE INVITED THE TWO
NEGLECTED STEPCHILDREN
TO COME ALONG.
>> Jeff: SERITA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK KRISTA MEANS WHEN SHE SAYS
YOU'RE NOT PLAYING THE GAME?
>> I JUST THINK IT'S SO FUNNY
BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN PLAYING
IT SO FAST AND FURIOUSLY THAT
WE UNSEATED ONE OF THE BEST
PLAYERS IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY
AND WE WANT TO STICK AND SEE IF
WE CAN TAKE THAT ALL THE WAY.
>> PLAYING THE GAME MEANS YOU
DON'T STICK WITH SIX THROUGH THE
ENTIRE GAME; YOU EVENTUALLY COME
DOWN TO FIVE THEN FOUR, THEN
THREE, THEN TWO, AND THEN
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO PLAY.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT HERE TO SIT
AROUND A CAMPFIRE AND MAKE
FRIENDS.
I'M HERE TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> YOU REALLY HAVEN'T PLAYED ANY
STRATEGIC GAME BECAUSE YOU
HAVEN'T HAD THOSE CONVERSATIONS.
YOU HAVEN'T REACHED OUT TO
PEOPLE.
YOU HAVEN'T DEVELOPED THAT
TRUST.
YOU'VE BEEN ABRASIVE THIS ENTIRE
TIME TO EVERYBODY.
THAT WAS YOUR STRATEGY.
>> WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO SAY?
"HEY, I GOT A GREAT IDEA, LET'S
VOTE OFF STEPHANIE."
>> HOW ABOUT YOU TALK TO SOMEONE
AND FORM A BOND AND ESTABLISH
SOME TRUST.
THAT'S STRATEGY.
>> Jeff: KRISTA, YOU'RE SAYING,
FINE, YOU'VE GOT ME OR STEPHANIE
TONIGHT BUT THEN THERE ARE SIX
OF YOU.
YOU'RE IMPLYING THERE IS NO
SUBALLIANCES IN THIS GROUP.
>> I THINK IF THERE ARE ANY,
IT'S IN PAIRS.
YOU OBVIOUSLY HAVE MIKE AND
STEVE WHO HAVE BEEN TIGHT FROM
THE BEGINNING.
AND THEN I THINK JULIE HAS
BECOME COMFORTABLE WITH STEVE.
AND THEN YOU HAVE SERITA AND
RALPH.
THEY SEEM TO BE TOGETHER.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE THAT LEAVES
DAVE.
BUT SEEMS TO BE TWOS.
SO WITH ME AND STEPHANIE HERE,
WHICH COULD BE A BIG FOUR, IF I
WAS IN THAT SIX, I WOULD BE
JUMPING ON ONE OF US.
>> Jeff: MIKE, THE TRADEOFF
FOR BEING SO CLEAR ABOUT WHO YOU
WANT TO VOTE OUT IS THEY NOW
COME TO TRIBAL WITH BOTH BARRELS
LOADED.
KRISTA JUST OUTED A WHOLE LOT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, JEFF.
THERE'S NO PROTECTING IT AT THIS
POINT.
HOWEVER, WHAT SHE DOESN'T KNOW
IS AMONGST OUR SIX
THERE HAS BEEN
LOTS OF TALK OF STRATEGY AND SHE
HAS BEEN THE ODD MAN OUT SO SHE
HASN'T SEEN ANY OF THAT.
>> Jeff: STEPHEN, IN ONE WAY,
IT'S EASY.
YOU'VE NARROWED IT DOWN TO
KRISTA OR STEPHANIE AND NOW YOU
HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHO ARE WE
GOING TO KEEP TO HELP US IN THE
NEXT CHALLENGE.
>> WELL, I WOULD HAVE PREFERRED
SOMEBODY ELSE MAKING THE CALLS
TODAY.
I WASN'T ABLE TO SAY ANYTHING
BUT I WOULD HAVE THROWN DOWN TO
HAVE DAVID MAKE THE CALL AND DO
THE PUZZLE.
>> Jeff: SO, STEPHANIE, WOULD
IT BE FAIR FOR THE TRIBE TO SAY
WE GAVE YOU THE MONEY SPOT.
YOU DIDN'T COME THROUGH.
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT SHOULD GO
HOME?
>> I JUST HAVE TO RELY ON MY
RECORD WITH THEM.
HOPEFULLY, I DID MY BEST IN
EVERY OTHER CHALLENGE.
AND I KNOW I HAVE.
I JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE THAT
THEY REALIZE THAT.
>> Jeff: KRISTA, DID YOU AND
STEPHANIE TALK ABOUT THE IDEA
TODAY THAT IT WAS ONE OF THE TWO
OF YOU GOING?
>> IT JUST BECOMES A REALITY
THAT, YOU KNOW, IT COULD BE ME.
IT COULD BE HER.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST WHO'S
GOING TO BE FIRST.
>> BUT WE STILL HAVE REDEMPTION
ISLAND SO WE HAVE TO KEEP THE
FAITH IN EACH OTHER ALIVE
BECAUSE WE HAVE NOTHING ELSE TO
HOLD ON TO.
>> Jeff: WELL, BASED ON WHAT
WE'VE HEARD TONIGHT, KRISTA OR
STEPHANIE, IT APPEARS ONE OF YOU
IS ABOUT TO BE SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
LET'S FIND OUT WHO IT IS GOING
TO BE.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JULIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff:
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, STEVE.
STEVE.
TWO VOTES STEVE.
KRISTA.
THREE VOTES KRISTA,
TWO VOTES STEVE.
KRISTA.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES KRISTA,
TWO VOTES STEVE.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,
KRISTA.
>> Jeff: KRISTA,
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS, TONIGHT,
YOU HAD AN EASY VOTE.
THE BAD NEWS-- KRISTA DIDN'T GO
QUIETLY.
THE QUESTION IS WHAT KIND OF
DAMAGE DID SHE DO TO THE
ALLIANCES WITHIN THIS TRIBE?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP. GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
AT REDEMPTION ISLAND, MATT'S
WINNING STREAK IS IN TROUBLE.
MATT, YOU NEED TO GET THAT BAG
OPEN.
>> I'M WORKING ON IT, PROBST.
>> Jeff: AND A GIRLS' SPA DAY.
>> IF YOU CAN MAKE YOURSELF BE
MORE COMFORTABLE, WHY NOT?
>> Jeff: CAUSES A PHILLIP
SHEPPARD MELT DOWN.
>> THIS IS NOT A PAGEANT.
GET OFF YOUR BUTTS AND HELP OUT
AROUND HERE.
I'M THE RED-HEADED STEPCHILD.
>> WALKING IN...
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE.
IT'S A REALLY SCARY, LONELY
FEELING.
BUT I HAVE A LIGHT AND A
STRENGTH WITHIN ME THAT NOT
ANYBODY CAN TAKE AWAY.
IT'S STARTING TO RAIN, AND IT'S
GOING TO BE COLD.