>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AT OMETEPE, BOSTON
ROB WAS THE UNDISPUTED TRIBE
LEADER.
>> I AM SO GLAD WE HAVE BOSTON
ROB.
HE'S AMAZING.
>> Jeff: AND HE FOUND A CLUE
TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I DON'T PLAN ON TELLING
ANYBODY ABOUT THE CLUE.
I WANT THE IDOL FOR ME.
>> Jeff: THE ONLY SPEED BUMPS
ON HIS ROAD TO THE END WERE
PHILLIP, WHO IS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> ROB GOING TO TRY TO PLAY ME
LIKE A FOOL AND I'M GOING TO
PLAY ALONG.
>> Jeff: AND CRIT TINA WHO IS
A CLEAR THREAT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO HAVE ROB
STICK AROUND THAT LONG.
>> Jeff: MEANWHILE, AT
ZAPATERA, RUSSELLs PLAYING A
FAMILIAR GAME-- HE SEARCHED FOR
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND
FORMED AN ALLIANCE OF THREE.
>> I CAN TRUST NOBODY BUT KRISTA
AND STEPHANIE.
>> Jeff: BUT RALPH HAD HIM BEAT
ON ALL FRONTS.
>> THIS IS NOT RUSSELL'S GAME.
THIS IS MY GAME.
>> Jeff: HE FOUND THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND GOT INTO AN
ALLIANCE OF SIX.
>> Jeff: RALPH'S CREW WAS SO
DETERMINED TO GET RUSSELL OUT,
THEY ACTURALLY THREW THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
OMETEPE WINS THEIR FIRST
CHALLENGE.
>> I'M DEALING WITH A BUNCH OF
BITCHES.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THE ZAPATERA DID WHAT NO OTHER
TRIBE HAD EVER DONE BEFORE--
THEY VOTED OUT RUSSELL.
RUSSELL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
HIS ALLIES ARE LEFT TO FEND FOR
THEMSELVES.
NOW RUSSELL'S LIFE IN THE GAME
HANGS BY A THREAD.
A DUEL AWAITS AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND, AND IF HE LOSES, HE'LL
BE OUT OF THE GAME FOR GOOD.
>> RUSSELL!
>> YES.
>> WHAT'S UP MAN?
>> RUSSELL HANTZ JUST WALKED
INTO MY CAMP.
I FIGURED I'D SEE HIM SOONER OR
LATER, BUT FIRST OFF.
MAN, THAT'S A BIT OF A SURPRISE.
>> WHAT THEY TOLD ME IS THE GIRL
BEAT YOU?
>> REALLY.
>> MY WHOLE TRIBE LOST THE
CHALLENGE ON PURPOSE JUST TO GET
RID OF ME.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I'VE
EVER BEEN VOTED OUT.
I WAS PISSED OFF.
I WANTED TO BITCH-SLAP EVERY ONE
OF THEM.
THE WHOLE TIME THEY WERE LYING
TO ME.
THEY TOLD ME FRANCESCA WAS HERE,
AND IT ISN'T.
IT'S THIS OTHER KID.
I MEAN, IT SUCTION BECAUSE
FRANCESCA MIGHT HAVE BEEN EASIER
TO BEAT IN CHALLENGES.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
HE'S A ROOKIE.
SO HE'S GOING TO BE NERVOUS AS
HELL DOING THE CHALLENGE AGAINST
ME, AND I'LL JUST TAKE HIM OUT.
>> YOU WERE ONE OF MY FAVORITE
PEOPLE TO WATCH.
>> NOW WE'RE BUNKING TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
BLINDSIDED BY ROB, BUNKING WITH
RUSSELL.
>> THAT'S KIND COOL.
RIGHT NOW THIS IS HIS HOUSE.
I'M ABOUT TO TAKE IT FROM HIM.
I'M GOING TO KEEP WINNING.
MY TRIBE IS GOING TO COME HERE
ONE AT A TIME, I'M GOING TO PICK
THEM OFF, AND I'M GOING TO MAKE
THEM SUFFER.
I'M GOING TO SAY, "SLEEP IN THE
MUD, FOOL."
>> THIS MORNING, WHILE EVERYBODY
WAS TRYING TO SLEEP,
PHILLIP WAS UP AT THE CRACK OF
DAWN SWEEPING.
HE'S JUST A PAIN IN THE BUTT.
HE'S SO ANNOYING.
AND HE'S SO WEIRD.
>> SAGGY-BOTTOM PANTIES.
SAGGY BOTTOMS.
>> I COULD GO 39 DAYS WITHOUT
SEEING THAT.
PHILLIP IS A PIECE OF WORK.
I MEAN, WHO COMES ON "SURVIVOR"
AND WEARS PINK TIGHTY-WHITEYS
WITH HIS STUFF JUST HANGING OUT
AND JUST FLOPPING AROUND
EVERYWHERE.
IT'S NOT ONLY DISTURBING.
IT'S ACTUALLY DISGUSTING.
IT'S LIKE YOUR DAD SHOULD HAVE
BOUGHT A NEW PAIR LIKE MONTHS
AGO.
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR FRIEND
COMING OVER TO PLAY AND SEEING
THAT.
>> THESE YOUNG PEOPLE OUT HERE,
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND ME.
THEY DON'T KNOW IF I'M A
CRIMINAL OR A SCHOOLTEACHER.
THEY DON'T KNOW HOW TO TAKE ME,
SO I'M A LITTLE FRUSTRATED OUT
HERE.
>> JUST GROSS.
>> GIVEN THAT THIS IS A SOCIAL
GAME, IT'S A HUGE DISADVANTAGE
FOR ME.
SO THERE HAS TO BE ANOTHER SIDE
OF ME THAT EMERGES, THE GUY
THAT'S UNDER COVER.
BECAUSE I'LL TELL THU MUCH-- I'M
PREPARED TO DO WHAT I NEED TO DO
TO WIN A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> IS IT BAD THAT I WANT THIS
DAY TO BE OVER ALREADY?
>> I JUST TRY TO REMOVE MYSELF
FROM THE CHAOS.
LAST NIGHT, RUSSELL WENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
SO NOW KRISTA AND I ARE HERE,
STUCK WITH ALL THESE GOOBERS,
AND NOT REALLY HAVING ANY FUN.
>> I JUST HOPE RUSSELL KILLS IT
BECAUSE THEY ARE GONNA BE SO
>> HE WILL KILL IT.
>> AT THIS POINT, I'M BUMMED,
BUT I'VE GOT TO PUT THE GAME
FACE ON BECAUSE ONE OF US IS
GOING TO GO HOME, UNLESS WE FIND
THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> THEM GIRLS,THEY'RE TOGETHER.
>> LET'S JUST KEEP OUR EYE ON
THEM.
>> I GOT IT UNDER CONTROL.
I HAD FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, I WAS PLANNING ON NOBODY
KNOWING, BUT STEPHANIE AND
KRISTA LEFT THE CAMP.
AND THOUGHT WELL, SHOOT,
RIGHT NOW IS THE FINE TIME TO
LET THEM ALL KNOW.
HEY, LISTEN TO ME, Y'ALL.
I FOUND THE IDOL.
AND RIGHT HERE IT IS.
MAN!
THEY ALL WAS TICKLED TO DEATH.
SO NOW I THINK I'VE GOT THEM
CAPTURED TO TAKE ME FURTHER IN
THE GAME.
I DIDN'T WANT THEM TO STRAY OFF
FROM ME.
WHEN YOU GOT A CATCH YOU HANG ON
TO IT.
I TOLD YOU ALL I HAD IT UNDER
CONTROL.
THE OTHER DAY--
>> I DIDN'T KNOW YOU MEANT
"UNDER CONTROL."
>> WE HAVE THE POWER RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE CONTROLLING THIS TRIBE BUT
I WOULD NOT BE SURPRISED IF WE
SAW RUSSELL BACK IN THIS GAME.
HOWEVER, NOW THAT WE HAVE THE
IDOL, IF AND WHEN HE COMES BACK,
IT'S GOING TO BE VERY, VERY
DIFFICULT FOR HIM TO GO DEEP
INTO THIS GAME.
>> THE EARLY BIRD GETS THE WORM.
IN THIS CASE, HE GET THE MAIL.
AGAIN, IT'S TIME TO CHOOSE WHO
WILL WITNESS THE DUEL.
YOU CAN CRAW STONES OR YOU CAN
ROCHAMBEAU, OR DISCUSS IT LIKE
CIVILIZED FOLKS.
REMEMBER, ONLY TWO CAN GO.
I'D LIKE TO GO.
HOW ABOUT YOU, KRISTINA, WOULD
YOU LIKE TO GO.
>> IF EVERYONE SAYS IT'S OKAY,
I'D LIKE TO GO.
>> YEAH, NO OBJECTION.
>> I DEFINITELY WANT TO VISIT
REDEMPTION ISLAND BECAUSE OF MY
BACKGROUND AS A SPECIAL AGENT
WITH THE UNITED STATES
GOVERNMENT.
I'M LOOKING FOR A LITTLE
INTEL TO HELP ME TO WIN THIS
GAME.
>> YOU'RE GOING.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS, I'M
GOING TO GO WITH RALPH.
>> HAVE FUN!
>> YES.
>> I AM SO EXCITED TO WATCH
THIS, ESPECIALLY WITH RALPH BY
MY SIDE AND IF I AM ABLE TO
WATCH RUSSELL WALK OFF AND GO
HOME, THAT WOULD BE MY MILLION
DOLLARS, ALMOST.
>> THIS DUEL IS GOING TO BE MAN
ON MAN, GOOD VERSUS EVIL TYPE
THING.
I LIKE MATT.
HE'S A GOOD GUY.
IF THIS WAS THE REAL WORLD, I'D
BE ROOTING FOR MATT, BUT IT'S
NOT.
THIS IS SURVIVOR.
>> RUSSELL HANTZ IS DEFINITELY
THE BIGGEST VILLAIN IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY HANDS DOWN,
BUT I'M FIGHTING TO HONOR MY
GOD, AND BECAUSE I WANT IT SO
DEEPLY AND SO TRULY I THINK I'M
GOING TO COME OUT ON TOP.
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND ARENA.
BOTH TRIBES HAVE SENT TWO
TRIBEMEMBERS TO WITNESS TODAY'S
DUEL.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU WILL STACK
A SERIES OF BLOCKS ON A
MULTILEVELED PLATFORM WHILE
AVOIDING TRIP WIRES, WHICH COULD
CAUSE YOUR BLOCKS TO TIP AND
FORCE YOU TO START OVER.
YOUR GOAL IS TO ARRANGE THE
BLOCKS SO THEY WILL FALL LIKE
DOMINOES, ULTIMATELY RELEASING
THE BALL, WHICH WILL SMASH A
TILE.
THE WINNER OF THIS DUEL LIVES TO
SEE ANOTHER DAY.
LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD.
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
TO STAY ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
ONE PERSON WILL GO BACK TO
REDEMPTION AFTER THIS CHALLENGE.
THE OTHER IS OUT OF THE GAME FOR
GOOD.
DO OUR DIE.
TO FURTHER COMPLICATE IT-- YOU
HIT THE ROPES, THE ROPES WILL
WIGGLE YOUR PLATFORM AND COULD
CAUSE YOUR BLOCKS TO FALL.
MAKING SURE YOU HAVE THEM SPACED
PROPERLY, THAT IS THE KEY.
YOU ONLY HAVE A CERTAIN NUMBER
OF BLOCKS, SO YOU CAN'T PUT THEM
TOO CLOSE TOGETHER OR YOU'LL RUN
OUT.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK IN THIS
DUEL.
MATT MAY HAVE A SLIGHT LEAD AT
THIS POINT.
RUSSELL'S GOING TO HAVE TO FILL
IN THOSE HOLES BECAUSE MATT IS
GETTING CLOSER.
>> I THINK I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: MATT GOING TO GIVE IT
A GO.
IF HE'S RIGHT, HE WILL STAY
ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
IF NOT, THE DOOR WILL OPEN FOR
RUSSELL.
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
MATT FALLS SHORT.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO RESTACK
HALF OF HIS LINE.
OPENS UP A HUGE OPPORTUNITY FOR
RUSSELL.
IT LOOKED GOOD.
HE WAS JUST SHORT ON ONE BLOCK.
>> ALL RIGHT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL THINKS HE HAS
IT AND HE'S GOING TO GIVE IT A
GO.
OH, HE JUST GETS THROUGH A BIT
OF A HOLE.
AND HE FALLS SHORT.
DOOR BACK OPEN FOR MATT.
BOTH GUYS NOW RACING TO RESTACK
THEIR BLOCKS.
YOU CAN'T ASK FOR MORE FROM A
MILLION-DOLLAR DUEL.
WIN THIS, YOUR SHOT AT THE MONEY
STAYS ALIVE.
LOSE IT, YOU ARE GOING HOME.
MATT HAS HIS RESTACKED.
>> THIS IS IT.
>> Jeff: HE'S GOING TO GIVE IT
A GO.
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
HE'S THROUGH THE TOUGH SPOT.
WILL IT MAKE IT?
MATT STAYS ALIVE!
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: MATT, CONGRATULATIONS.
ONCE AGAIN, YOU SEIZE THE
MOMENT, AND YOU STAY ALIVE IN
THIS GAME.
RUSSELL, BRAND NEW FOR YOU.
YOU ARE OUT OF THIS GAME.
RUSSELL, YOU HAVE BARED YOUR
SOUL OUT HERE IN WAYS THAT VERY
FEW HAVE.
YOU HAVE PLAYED A VERY, VERY
STRONG GAME TWO TIMES.
( CRYING )
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
IT'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL IS IT SADNESS
THAT YOU'RE OUT OF THE GAME?
IS IT EMBARRASSMENT AT FINALLY
LOSING?
>> NO.
I RESPECT THIS GAME TOO MUCH TO
GO OUT THIS WAY.
AND, YOU KNOW, PEOPLE LIKE MY
TRIBE THAT THROWS A CHALLENGE
JUST TO GET RID OF ME BECAUSE
I'M RUSSELL, NOT EVEN WORRIED
ABOUT BOSTON ROB AND HIS TEAM
AND NUMBERS.
SO IT'S HARD TO BE A
PROFESSIONAL QUARTERBACK AND
HAVE PEEWEE LEAGUERS ON YOUR
TEAM BECAUSE I'VE GOT TO RUN THE
BALL, I'VE GOT TO CATCH THE
BALL, I'VE GOT TO THROW THE
BALL.
I HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING.
>> I DON'T REALLY THINK SO.
I THINK WE'VE DONE GREAT.
RUSSELL WOULD NOT SHOW US THE
HIDDEN CLUE OR WHERE THE IDOL
WAS HIDDEN.
BUT THAT'S BESIDE THE POINT.
I'D ALREADY FOUND IT IN 15
SECONDS IN THE GAME.
HE'S GOT COMPETITION ON HIS
HANDS NOW.
>> LISTEN TO HIM TALKING.
HE SAID HE FOUND IT 15 SECONDS
IN THE GAME.
DID YOU SHOW ME THE IDOL?
>> THERE YOU GO, GUYS.
HE HAS THE IDOL.
>> DON'T DO THIS RALPH.
DON'T DO THIS.
>> I FAKED YOU.
>> HE FAKED ME.
>> Jeff: WOW!
>> HE HAS THE IDOL.
HE'S SUCH A GOOD PLAYER, HE'S
TELLING YOU EVERYTHING HE HAS
RIGHT NOW.
TAKE HIM OUT.
>> DID I SHOW YOU ONE?
SEE HOW I BLUFFED HIM?
>> Jeff: SO, RALPH, YOU'RE
SAYING YOUR WHOLE STORY OF 15
SECONDS IN WAS ACTUALLY A LIE.
>> COULD BE, COULD NOT BE.
>> IT WAS NOT A LIE.
IT WAS NOT A LIE.
I EARNED MY LIVING DISCERNING
WHETHER OR NOT SOMEONE IS
TELLING THE TRUTH OR NOT.
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
>> AND YOU HAVE AN IDOL.
YOU'LL PROBABLY GET AN
OPPORTUNITY TO DO 2 USE IT IF I
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
>> AND SHE'S IN CHARGE.
AND MIKE AND STEVE, THEY'RE A
TEAM AS WELL.
>> I'M GLAD I CAME.
>> YOU SEE, JEFF, I HAD TO STAY
IN THIS GAME SOMEHOW.
NOW THROUGH THESE TWO I CAN STAY
IN THIS GAME.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> IF THEIR TRIBE WINS, THEY
TAKE OUT THESE DUMMIES, MORE
POWER TO ME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
RUSSELL, YOUR SHOT AT MAKING IT
TO THE FINAL FOUR A THIRD TIME
IS OVER.
YOU ARE OUT OF THIS GAME.
YOU CAN DROP YOUR BUFF IN THE
FIRE ON YOUR WAY OUT.
>> SEE YOU LATER, MAN.
>> BYE, RUSS.
>> TAKE CARE, RUSS.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> THANKS FOR THE INFO.
>> IT'S JUST TERRIBLE WHEN YOU
PLAY WITH PEOPLE THAT DIDN'T
REALLY COME HERE TO PLAY THE
GAME.
THEY JUST CAME HERE MAYBE FOR
FAME OR JUST FOR THE MONEY.
THIS IS MY LAST TIME PLAYING
THIS GAME.
THAT'S IT.
I HAVE NOTHING ELSE TO PROVE TO
MYSELF OR TO MY FAMILY.
MATT, I GIVE HIM PROPS, BEATING
ME, AND I HOPE HE GOES ALL THE
WAY.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: MATT, YOU SURVIVED
ANOTHER DUEL, MY FRIEND.
YOUR JOURNEY TO GET BACK INTO
THIS GAME CONTINUES.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION AND
AWAIT YOUR NEXT OPPONENT.
>> GOOD JOB, MATT!
>> GOOD JOB, MATT.
>> GO!
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
CAN HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
AS ALWAYS, WHAT YOU CHOOSE TO
SHARE WITH YOUR TRIBEMATES, IS
UP TO YOU.
>> THANKS TO RUSSELL I'VE
LEARNED SOME VERY INTERESTING
THINGS TODAY AND I'M GOING TO
USE THAT TO HELP ME.
AFTER ALL IT IS THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR--" OUTLAST, OUTWIT,
OUTPLAY.
THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE TO TRY TO
DO.
>> WE SHOULD HAVE A BEACH DAY
TODAY.
IT'S GOING TO BE A BEACH DAY.
>> I'M SO GLAD THEY VOLUNTEERED.
>> WE CAN PUT A BLANKET ON THE
BEACH, A CRAB BOIL, RICE.
>> SOUND GOOD TO ME.
>> I STARTED THINKING I NEED TO
FIND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL BEFORE
KRISTINA FINDS IT AGAIN.
I ALREADY HAD THE CLUE AND I HAD
A GOOD IDEA IT WAS ON THIS SIDE
OF CAMP AND I NEEDED TO GET
EVERYBODY OUT OF CAMP FOR THE
DAY.
SO I CREATED THIS GAME.
WE'RE CALLING IT ROYAL
TREATMENT.
THE WINNER GETS WHATEVER THEY
WANT.
YOU CAN GET YOUR RICE SERVED TO
YOU BY WHOEVER YOU WANT.
SO I'M TRYING TO THINK HOW AM I
GOING TO GET AWAY FROM EVERYBODY
AFTER I'M THE ONE THAT PLANNED
THIS WHOLE BEACH DAY.
MY STOMACH'S BOTHERING ME A
LITTLE BIT, TOO.
>> IT IS.
>> MAYBE, LIKE, CONSTIPATED?
>> OH, NO.
>> SO I TELL THEM I'M HAVING A
LITTLE BIT OF TROUBLE MOVING
THINGS DOWN IN THAT AREA, YOU
KNOW, AND I FEEL LIKE SOMETHING
MIGHT BE HAPPENING.
>> HOW FAR DOWN?
OR WE'RE GOING WAY PAST.
THAT'S A LONG TREK, BRO.
>> THIS LOOKS GOOD.
>> SO I BRING THEM TO THE NICE
PART OF THE BEACH WHERE THE SAND
IS REALLY NICE, AND IMMEDIATELY,
GRANT HEADS INTO THE OCEAN,
PERFECT, I DON'T HAVE TO EVEN
LOOK GRANT IN THE EYE.
I DON'T HAVE TO MAKE AN EXCUSE.
THEY'LL COVER FOR ME.
SO I LOOK AT THE GIRLS AND I
SAID, "IT'S TIME.
I HAVE TO TRY TO RELIEVE
MYSELF."
I KNEW I HAD A LIMITED AMOUNT OF
TIME.
SO I HIGH-TAILED IT BACK TO
CAMP, AND IT'S LIKE GAME ON.
WHERE IS THIS THING?
THE CLUE, IT BASICALLY TOLD ME
IT'S SOMEWHERE ON THE ISLAND,
EITHER IN A TREE, UNDER A ROCK,
IN THE SAND, OR IN A LOG.
WHAT A GREAT CLUE.
THIS IS A REALLY WEIRD TREE.
THERE'S ROCKS.
IT SHOULD BE HERE.
I'M DIGGING THROUGH ROCKS.
I'M CLIMBING TREES.
I'M LOOKING EVERYWHERE.
AND I'M HAVING A REALLY TOUGH
TIME.
SO I JUST STARTED SEARCHING FROM
TREE TO TREE.
>> WHERE'S ROB?
>> AT THIS POINT, I'VE ALREADY
BEEN GONE FOR 15 MINUTES.
I NEED TO GET BACK TO THE BEACH.
OTHERWISE, IT'S GOING TO LOOK
SUSPICIOUS.
WHERE IS IT?
YOU KNOW, THERE'S PROBABLY ABOUT
40 TREES IN OUR IMMEDIATE AREA.
AND I THINK IT WAS MAYBE 38 OR
39 I FINALLY LOOKED UP.
BINGO.
DING-DING!
WE HAVE A WINNER.
BABY, MAYBE I LEARNED SOMETHING
SINCE LAST TIME.
AS FOR MY PLANS FOR IT, RIGHT
NOW, I'M NOT SURE.
>> DO YOU FEEL BETTER?
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
IT.
BUT ONE THING I DO KNOW IS THAT
WITH THIS IMMUNITY IDOL, THIS
TIME I'M GOING TO MAKE IT 39
DAYS AND WIN.
>> OH!
>> YOU BLEW IT!
YOU BLEW IT!
>> I WAS GOING FOR THE WIN.
>> HI, THERE!
>> HEY!
>> THAT WAS CRAZY!
>> YEAH, SO MUCH STUFF WENT
DOWN.
FIRST THEY COME OUT, AND THEY
STARTED THE CHALLENGE, WHICH WAS
REALLY HARD.
BUT IN THE END, MATT WON.
>> WOW.
>> I AM STOKED THAT RUSSELL'S
OUT OF THE GAME.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
OUR PLAN WORKED.
AND I AM SO RELIEVED THAT HE'S
NOT GOING TO COME BACK AND GET
ME.
HE'S GONE!
YA!
>> RUSSELL WAS DEVASTATED.
LIKE, HE WAS CRYING SO I
HYSTERICALLY.
>> HE WAS?
>> IT WAS AWFUL TO SEE.
>> IT WAS TERRIBLE.
>> AND THEN HE FOUND HIS
RUSSELLNESS, AND JUST BASICALLY
THREW BACK THE COVERS ON
EVERYTHING ABOUT OUR CAMP.
LIKE, HE JUST STARTED THROWING
OUT THE HIT.
THE POINT IS, HE'S OUT.
>> SEE YOU, PUNK.
>> OH, NOW YOU'RE GOING TOO
MUCH.
>> STEPHANIE AND KRISTA SHOWED
SOME EMOTION THAT INDICATED THEY
WERE STILL IN CAMP RUSSELL,
WHICH I CAN UNDERSTAND.
I THINK THE FACT THAT EVERYBODY
ELSE WAS KIND OF DANCING ON HIS
GRAVE, YOU KNOW, ADDED INSULT TO
INJURY.
>> THAT MATT KID SOUNDS PRETTY
TOUGH.
I'M AMAZED THAT THEY GOT RID OF
HIM.
>> PEOPLE DO SOME DUMB STUFF,
YOU KNOW, LIKE THROW CHALLENGES
WHEN THEY'RE AHEAD.
>> THE TRIBE IS MUCH STRONGER.
HE WAS BREAKING DOWN THE SYNERGY
IN OUR TRIBE.
>> IN THE GAME OF NUMBERS,
SYNERGY IS THE LAST THING YOU
SHOULD BE WORRIED ABOUT.
>> I DISAGREE.
WHEN YOU'RE BATTLING AGAINST THE
OTHER TEAM I THINK SYNERGY AND
CHEMISTRY IS THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING.
WE HAD TO LOSE ONE AT ONE POINT
TO GET RID OF THE PLAGUE.
>> OKAY, LISTEN, WHEN WE GO
BACK, WE'RE GOING TO TELL THEM
ABOUT THE BREAKDOWN THAT RUSSELL
HAD.
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO TELL THEM
IS WHO HAS IMMUNITY IDOLS.
YOU'RE GOING TO LET ME GO TO
ROB.
THIS IS GOOD ENOUGH INTEL THAT
YOU SHOULD MOVE FROM BEING THE
NEXT ONE GOING HOME TO MAYBE THE
FOURTH.
ROB HAS TOLD ME WE'RE IN AN
ALLIANCE BUT I HAVE A FEELING HE
TOLD MATT THE SAME THING.
SO FOR ME I KNOW I'M THE ODD MAN
OUT.
IS IT BETTER FOR ME TO HAVE
KRISTINA STAY IN THE GAME?"
WELL, IF I COULD PULL ONE OTHER
PERSON THEN SHE WOULD BE VERY
VALUABLE TO ME.
>> WELL, YOU HAVE EXPERIENCE IN
THESE CONVERT MATTERS, PHIL, SO
WHATEVER YOU THINK.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO TRY
TO GET YOU MOVED UP ON THE LIST.
>> PHIL TOLD ME HE WAS GOING TO
WITHHOLD THE NAMES OF THE PEOPLE
UNTIL ROB TOOK US TO THE MERGE,
AND THEN AT THAT POINT REVEAL
THE NAMES, KIND OF LIKE
BLACKMAIL.
THE SPECIALIST THINKS HE'S
RUNNING THE SHOW, BUT THE
SPECIALIST IS JUST ONE, BIG
WINDBAG.
SO I'M JUST GOING TO SIT BACK
AND LET HIM DIG HIS OWN GRAVE
RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU GUYS MISSED A DOOZY
TODAY.
RUSSELL WENT HOME.
AND IT WAS UGLY!
RUSSELL STARTS CRYING.
I MEAN, IT WAS A TOTAL MELTDOWN.
>> HE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING ABOUT
IDOLS LIKE IF HE HAD ONE OR
ANYTHING?
>> NO, THAT WAS IT.
SO IT WAS REALLY WEIRD.
>> SO I'M GONNA REVEAL
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHEN YOU SAID WHAT HAPPENED
THAT'S NOT WHAT HAPPENED?
>> NO.
NUMBER ONE, RUSSELL GOT IN SUCH
A MELTDOWN HE NAMED WHO THE
LEADER IS OVER THERE.
WHO'S RUNNING THE SHOW.
>> WHO'S THE LEADER?
>> I'M GOING TO RUN THROUGH THE
LIST.
HE NAMED-- JUST LISTEN, ROB!
LET ME TELL THE STORY!
>> ALL RIGHT, TELL THE STORY.
>> OKAY.
HE STARTED NAMING WHO HAD AN
IDOL.
THEN RUSSELL NAMED THE TWO
ALLIANCES.
NOW, DO YOU THINK IF I REVEAL
ALL THAT INFORMATION TO YOU BY
NAME YOU WOULD BE ABLE TO DO
SOMETHING FOR KRISTINA?
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD TELL IT TO
US ANYWAY BECAUSE WE'RE IN AN
ALLIANCE.
>> I KNOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT KRISTINA
HAS TO DO WITH IT.
PHILLIP IS LOBBYING FOR KRISTINA
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
I'M LIKE, HEY, DUMB ASS!
AREN'T YOU IN MY ALLIANCE?
DON'T YOU WORK FOR ME?
NOW YOU'RE TELLING ME WHO I
SHOULD GRANT FAVORS TO?
BIG MISTAKE, PHILLIP.
>> IF YOU HAD THIS INFORMATION
IN YOUR HAND, WOULD IT HELP HER
CHANCES?
>> ABSOLUTELY, ABSOLUTELY.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE
WHO'S RUNNING THE SHOW?
>> THE TALL GIRL.
>> THE ONE WITH THE BLACK HAT?
>> THE BLACK HAT.
>> AND RALPH FOUND AN IDOL.
>> IF HE FELT SECURE, WHY WOULD
HE EVER WANT TO KEEP KRISTINA SO
PHILLIP KNOWS WHERE HE'S
STANDING.
THIS INFORMATION IS VERY
HELPFUL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> YEAH, I THINK IT'S EXTREMELY
HELPFUL.
AS FAR AS PHILLIP GOES, AFTER
THIS, THERE'S NO TRUST
WHATSOEVER NOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG IT'S GOING
TO TAKE, BUT THIS CAN'T GO ON
MUCH LONGER WE CAN'T TRUST THAT
DUDE.
WE HAVE TO GET RID OF HIM.
>> I KNOW, BRO, I KNOW.
>> WHAT DO WE GOT?
>> WE GOT MAIL.
>> READY?
TEAMWORK AND RUGGEDNESS ARE THE
SOLUTIONS TO WIN.
CREATIVITY AND PERFORMANCE ARE
GOOD PLACES TO BEGIN.
SENDING A TRIBEMATE AWAY IS
NEVER IN YOUR PLAN.
WHAT YOU'LL NEED TODAY IS TRUST
IN YOUR HANDS.
>> WE GOT THIS ONE.
WE'RE BUILDING SOMETHING.
>> WE GOT THE MASTER BUILDER.
>> I'M A LITTLE SUPERSTICIOUS,
AND I DO BELIEVE IN
KARMA.
SO IT IS SO IMPORTANT FOR US TO
WIN THIS ONE, TO BUILD UP
MOMENTUM.
WE THREW THAT LAST CHALLENGE,
AND I HOPE IT DOESN'T COME BACK
TO BITE US.
WE HAVE TO WIN THIS TODAY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
KRISTINA, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
ON DAY ONE, BOTH TRIBES WERE
GIVEN A CRAFTSMAN TOOL KIT FULL
OF TOOLS.
TODAY'S CHALLENGE IS GOING TO
TEST HOW ADEPT YOU'VE BECOME AT
USING THOSE TOOLS.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL MAKE YOUR WAY
OVER A BALANCE BEAM WHERE YOU'LL
USE A CROW BAR TO OPEN A CRATE.
YOU WILL RETRIEVE A SHOVEL.
YOU WILL DIG TO FIND AN AXE.
YOU WILL THE AXE TO CHOP THROUGH
A ROPE RELEASING TWO SAWS.
YOU WILL THEN SAW THROUGH A WALL
CREATING PLANKS.
YOU'LL USE THE PLANKS TO
COMPLETE A RAMP, ALCOHOL GET THE
ENTIRE TRIBE TO THE TOP OF THE A
PLATFORM WHERE YOU MUST HAMMER
THREE NAILS BREAKING THREE
TILES.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET THEIR
CRAFTSMAN TOOL KIT ON TOP OF
THAT TABLE WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES!
>> OH!
>> SHOOT!
>> Jeff: A BARBECUE SET.
ALSO PROVIDED BY SEARS.
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO BARBECUE,
INCLUDING THE FOOD.
YOU HAVE STEAK, SAUSAGE, BREAD,
VEGETABLES.
WORTH PLAYING FOR.
>> YES!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA, YOU HAVE
ONE EXTRA PERSON.
GOING TO SIT SOMEBODY OUT IN
THIS CHALLENGE, WHO IS IT GOING
TO BE?
>> KRISTA.
>> Jeff: KRISTA, TAKE A SPOT
ON THE BENCH.
GIVE EVERYBODY ELSE A MINUTE TO
FIGURE OUT WHO IS GOING TO DO
WHAT AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
FOR REWARD AND IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GO, ROB, GO, ROB!
>> Jeff: IT'S ROB AND RALPH AT
THE FIRST STAGE.
>> GO JOB, ROB.
>> Jeff: USING THE CROW BAR.
>> COME ON RALPH!
>> Jeff: RALPH NOT MESSING
AROUND.
HE'S GOT THE SHOVEL AND HE'S
HEADING BACK.
ROB HAS THE SHOVEL OUT.
JULIE NOW GOING TO USE THE
SHOVEL TO DIG.
GRANT NOW GOING TO USE THE
SHOVEL TO DIG FOR OMETEPE.
GRANT IS FAST AND MADE UP A LOT
OF TIME.
GRANT TEARING THROUGH THAT DIRT.
>> COME ON, JULIE.
>> DEEPER, GIRL, DEEPER!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A
HATCHET.
>> YOU GOT IT, GRANT, GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: OKAY, JULIE HAS THE
HATCHET FOR ZAPATERA.
>> GOOD JOB, GRANT!
YEAH!
>> Jeff: GRANT HAS IT
FOR OMETEPE.
RALPH NOW COMING OUT FOR
ZAPATERA.
>> LET'S GO, BOSTON ROB.
>> Jeff: RALPH ATTACKING THAT
LOG.
BOSTON ROB NOW IN IT ON.
RALPH HAD A BIT OF A LEAD AND
HE'S USING IT.
RALPH IS REALLY WORKING THROUGH
THAT LOG.
>> YOU'RE ALMOST THERE!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE TRYING TO GET
THROUGH THAT ROPE TO RELEASE TWO
SAWS.
KEEP IT GOING.
RALPH HAS RELEASED THE SAWS.
HE'S HEADED BACK.
ROB STILL WORKING.
UNTIE THOSE SAWS.
ROB NOT GIVING UP.
>> COME ON STEVE, KEEP IT GOING.
>> Jeff: ROB, VERY CLOSE.
ROB'S RELEASED THE SAWS.
>> COME ON STEVE AND MIKE!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP AND GRANT
NOW RACING OUT.
>> COME ON PHILLIP!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP AND GRANT
TRYING TO UNTIE THE SAWS.
THEY'RE NOW IN ON THE SIGN.
MIKE AND STEVE SAWING FOR
ZAPATERA.
THEY'VE GOT A HEAD START.
GRANT AND PHILLIP ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO MAKE UP SOME TIME.
>> WORK TOGETHER!
>> LET ME GET IT.
>> Jeff: MIKE IS GOING TO TAKE
OVER ON STEVE'S SIDE.
GRANT AND PHILLIP VERY SLOW
ON THE SIGN.
>> MIKE AND STEVE MAKING QUICK
WORK OF THIS WALL.
GRANT AND PHILLIP ARE FALLING
BEHIND.
>> YES!
>> COME ON, PHILLIP!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP AND GRANT
EXHAUSTED.
THIS IS NOT EASY.
ZAPATERA HAS ONE PLANK LEFT.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
MIKE AND STEVE HEADED BACK NOW.
STEPHANIE AND SERENA HEADING ON
THE FOR ZAPATERA TO PUT THE
PLANKS INTO THE RAMP.
>> GO, GIRLS, GO!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP AND GRANT ARE
ON THAT FINAL PLANK
FOR OMETEPE.
YOU NEED TO DIG, PHILLIP!
THEY HAVE IT!
OMETEPE IS STILL IN THIS.
>> THIS DOESN'T FIT!
>> COME ON, GIRLS!
DAMN!
>> Jeff: ROB AND KRISTINA
HEADING OUT FOR OMETEPE.
STEPHANIE AND SERENA NEED TO
HURRY UP.
ROB AND KRISTINA GAINING GROUND.
>> NOT THIS ONE, NEXT ONE.
3 AND ONE.
>> Jeff: STEPHANIE AND SERENA
VERY CLOSE.
STEPHANIE AND SERENA FINISH
THEIR PLANKS.
ROB AND KRISTINA GETTING CLOSE.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> YOU GUYS, SLOW DOWN.
THEY'RE ALMOST DONE.
>> GO, GO, GO, COME ON!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA UP THE PLANK.
>> GOOD JOB, ROB.
GOOD JOB, KRISTINA!
>> Jeff: ROB AND KRISTINA
FINISHED THEIR PLANKS.
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO BE HERE.
HERE COMES OMETEPE.
WE'VE GOT A CHALLENGE.
>> I GOT IT!
>> THEY'RE RIGHT ON OUR ASS!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY'S GOT TO
GET HERE, GOT TO GET ON THE MAT.
STEPHANIE WORKING ON THE KNOTS
FOR ZAPATERA.
>> ASHLEY WORKING ON THE KNOTS
FOR OMETEPE.
>> FOCUS, SHHH!
>> Jeff: ASHLEY IS MAKING
PROGRESS.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
>> JUST PULL OUT, JUST PULL IT
OUT!
>> GO, RALPH, GO.
>> Jeff: STEPHANIE HAS RELEASED
IT.
RALPH WILL USE THE HAMMER.
NO PROBLEM.
ZAPATERA WINS REWARD!
AND IMMUNITY.
>> GET UP ON THERE AND CROW.
>> A ROOSTER, BABY.
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA, IMMUNITY
ONCE AGAIN IS YOURS.
ALONG WITH A PRETTY DECENT
REWARD.
ZAPATERA, COME GET YOUR REWARD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> DON'T DROP IT!
>> HELL, NO!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, OMETEPE,
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS!
ABOUT TIME!
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE A FEAST!
>> CAN YOU SMELL THE PEPPER?
SMELL.
>> THIS VICTORY TRULY WAS
EXPONENTIAL.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN THIS HUNGRY IN
MY LIFE.
I HAVEN'T THOUGHT ABOUT SEX IN
TWO WEEKS.
ALL I'M THINKING ABOUT IS FOOD.
>> LET'S JUST START COOKING.
>> IT WAS AWESOME.
WE HAD RED MEAT AND SOME KIND OF
SAUSAGE LINK, BELL PEPPERS.
IT TASTED GREAT.
I SUCKED STUFF OUT OF MY
FINGERNAILS THAT HAVEN'T BEEN
CLEANED SINCE I GOT HERE.
>> WE ARE THE STRONGER TEAM.
>> THERE IS DEFINITELY A GOOD
MOOD ROLLING THROUGH THE CAMP.
I DEFINITELY DON'T WISH ILL UPON
THE OTHER TRIBE, BUT I'M REALLY
GLAD WE'RE NOT SITTING IN THEIR
SHOES NOW TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO ABOUT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
>> SO, HOW ABOUT A BRIEF TRIBAL
MEETING REAL QUICKLY HERE?
I KNOW WE'RE ALL FEELING A
LITTLE DOWN RIGHT NOW.
WE WOULD HAVE LIKED TO HAVE WON.
THAT SAID, I THOUGHT WE DID
PRETTY GOOD OVERALL.
YOU KNOW, WE ALL PUT FORTH A
GREAT EFFORT.
OKAY.
ANYBODY GOT ANYTHING?
LET'S GET TO IT.
>> MAN, WE CAN'T WIN A
CHALLENGE.
IT'S TOUGH ALREADY, AND PHILLIP,
HE'S NEVER ONE TO SHY AWAY FROM
A MOMENT IN THE SUN.
I MEAN, AT THIS POINT, THERE'S,
LIKE, AN UTTER MALICE TOWARDS
HIM.
THAT'S PALPABLE.
>> ARE YOU GETTING READY TO POUR
IT.
>> YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO POUR IT.
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO DO IT?
>> NOPE , I GOT IT.
>> I GOT TO SEE THIS.
JUST BE VERY CAREFUL.
MOVE AWAY.
LIKE YOUR FEET--
>> PHILLIP, I CANNOT STAND HIM.
LIKE, CAN'T EVEN LOOK AT HIM.
THAT'S HIGHWAY BAD I CAN'T STAND
HIM.
AND I THINK WE'RE ALL ON THE
SAME PAGE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, WE'VE GOT TO GO
TO TRIBAL TONIGHT SO WE MIGHT AS
WELL MAKE THE BEST OF IT.
I JUST HOPE PHILLIP GOES HOME!
>> GET YOUR ASS UP HERE.
>> WHEN I COME BACK FROM A LOSS,
THE VERY LAST THING THAT I
REALLY WANT TO HAVE TO ENDURE IS
PHILLIP'S YAMMERING.
GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT
I'M THINKING IT'S MYSELF OR
PHILLIP GOING HOME.
I'M ON THE WRONG SIDE OF THE
NUMBERS IN THIS TRIBE.
I HAVE BEEN SINCE DAY ONE.
AT THE SAME TIME, THEY MIGHT
VOTE FOR PHILLIP BECAUSE HE DOES
ANNOY EVERYBODY.
SO I THINK I HAVE A GOOD CHANCE,
BUT IF I HAD THE IDOL IN MY
POCKET, I'D FEEL BETTER.
>> WHEN WE WON THE REWARD, THERE
MUST HAVE BEEN A CLUE.
I'D BE SURPRISED IF THEY HAVEN'T
FOUND IT.
>> WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE?
>> YOU.
>> KRISTINA IS KIND OF ACTING
WEIRD.
SHE'S NOT FRANTICALLY SEARCHING
FOR THE IDOL, WHICH IS VERY
STRANGE.
COULD MEAN THAT SHE HAS IT.
COULD MEAN THAT SHE DOESN'T.
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE GOES, "WELL, I GUESS THE
IDOL'S IN PLAY NOW GAIN."
AND I'M LIKE, "WHAT MAKES YOU
THINK THAT?"
AND SHE'S LIKE, "WELL, SOMEBODY
MUST HAVE FOUND THE CLUE."
>> OH, SHE THINKS ONE OF US
FOUND IT?
>> SHE THINKS WE HAVE THE IDOL.
OR SHE DOES HAVE IT.
DUDE, THIS IS SO TRICKY.
>> EXACTLY.
>> LIKE I CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
APPARENTLY KRISTINA HAS BEEN
SNOOPING AROUND ABOUT THE IDOL.
SHE'S DANGEROUS.
AS MUCH AS EVERYBODY HATES
PHILLIP HE'S LESS OF A THREAT TO
ME THAN KRISTINA IS.
THIS IS WHAT I THINK.
WE SEND HER ASS HOME.
WHY TAKE A CHANCE?
JUST SPLIT.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE IT AWAY
THAT I HAVE THE IDOL.
I WANT THEM TO THINK KRISTINA
HAS IT SO WE'RE GOING TO SPLIT
THE VOTES.
WE'RE GOING TO THROW THREE VOTES
ON CHRISTINE, TWO VOTES ON
PHILLIP AND IF EVERYBODY DOES
WHAT THEY'RE TOLD, KRISTINA WILL
BE VOTED OUT.
>> WITH PHILLIP, IT'S JUST MORE
STRESSFUL.
HAVING HIM AROUND.
>> HE'S A PAIN IN THE ASS.
HE'S A HAZARD, MAN.
>> HE'S A TICKING TIMED BOMB.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S WHAT SCARES ME.
>> THE PLAN IS AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT TO GET RID OF KRISTINA,
BUT I THINK IT'S A MISTAKE.
PHILLIP IS JUST A LOOSE CANNON.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S GOING
TO DO.
I DON'T TRUST HIM, DUDE.
>> I DON'T, EITHER.
>> THE SOONER WE GET RID OF--
>> I JUST WONDER-- LIKE, WHO
KNOWS HOW TO PLAY THE GAME
BETTER?
>> I'M TELLING YOU, I WOULD FEEL
A LOT BETTER FOR ALL OF US IF WE
WERE GONE.
WE CAN DEAL WITH KRISTINA, I
THINK?
>> CAN WE?
KRISTINA'S NO SLOUCH, MAN.
GRANT, HE WANTS TO GET RID OF
PHILLIP TONIGHT, AND THOSE GIRLS
ARE OBSESSED WITH GETTING
PHILLIP OUT.
SO IT QUITE CONCEIVABLY COULD BE
THAT SOMEBODY WITHIN MY ALLIANCE
MIGHT BE WILLING TO FLIP AND
VOTE OUT PHILLIP.
HONESTLY, AS LONG ASHLEY STAYS
ON BOARD AND GRANT STAYS ON
BOARD THEN WE HAVE NOTHING TO
FEAR.
HOPEFULLY, ALL THESE GUYS GET
NICE IN LINE LIKE THEY SHOULD
AND DO AS THEY'RE TOLD.
IF NOT, I'M NOT IN CONTROL OF MY
TRIBE AFTER ALL.
>> SO I JUST WANNA KNOW WHAT AM
I DOING TONIGHT?
>> I THINK IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS.
WE'RE ALL VOTING FOR KRISTINA.
>> OKAY.
>> SURE ENOUGH, ROB WANTS TO
VOTE KRISTINA.
CLEARLY, HE'S NOT A MAN OF HIS
WORD.
SO I NEED TO TAKE CONTROL OF MY
OWN FATE AND AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
BE READY TO MAKE THE MOVES YOU
NEED TO MAKE TO SURVIVE.
>> I'M READY TO GO.
>> BECAUSE WHO KNOWS?
I COULD BE THE REAL TARGET.
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN IN THE GAME
OF "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: KRISTINA, BOTH TIMES
THAT YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN HERE TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU'VE BEEN ON
THE HOT SEAT.
FEEL THAT AGAIN TONIGHT?
>> SURE, ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S HAPPENING
THAT'S ALWAYS GOT YOU IN
TROUBLE?
>> I MEAN, I FELT LIKE I STARTED
OFF ON THE WRONG SIDE OF THE
NUMBERS.
BUT I'M A FIGHTER, AND I DON'T
GIVE UP, AND I'M DETERMINED.
I'LL KEEP TRYING, YOU KNOW.
I WANT TO STAY.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, HOW DO YOU
FEEL ABOUT SECOND CHANCES?
>> I THINK SECOND CHANCES ARE
GREAT.
I THINK KRISTINA'S A REALLY NICE
PERSON, YOU KNOW.
JUST HAVE TO SEE.
>> Jeff: GRANT, CAN PEOPLE
CHANGE IN THIS GAME?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, OF COURSE.
EVERYBODY HERE IS PRETTY LAID
BACK ANDAISE TO GET ALONG WITH,
SO YOU CAN DEFINITELY GET A
SECOND CHANCE.
>> BUT, TO BE FAIR, I THINK,
KRISTINA REALLY JUST JOINED THIS
TRIBE.
FOR THE FIRST EIGHT DAYS WE WERE
OUT HERE, I DON'T THINK SHE
REALLY, LIKE, WAS A PART OF US.
THE REAL QUESTION IS, IS IT TOO
LATE?
OR ARE PEOPLE WILLING TO GIVE
HER A SHOT?
>> Jeff: KRISTINA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK THE TRIBE SHOULD DO
TONIGHT?
>> I THINK THE TRIBE SHOULD VOTE
OUT WHO THEY CONSIDER TO BE THE
WEAKEST LINK IN THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: AND HOW DO YOU DEFINE
"WEAK?"
>> I THINK WEAK IN THIS CASE
MIGHT BE DISRUPTIVENESS.
>> Jeff: WHO QUALIFIES AS
BEING DISRUPTIVE?
>> OH, I THINK PHIL'S A LITTLE
DISRUPTIVE.
I THINK HE'S A LITTLE ASSERTIVE,
AND I THINK IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE
FOR SOME PEOPLE AT TIMES.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, IS THAT
SOMETHING YOU'VE FACED IN LIFE
BEFORE, BEING A LITTLE
DISRUPTIVE?
>> NO, I WOULDN'T CHARACTERIZE
IT AS THAT AT ALL.
I'M ACTUALLY A DOER.
AND I'M ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE THAT
IF YOU'RE NOT ABOUT PULLING YOUR
SHARE AND YOU SHOW UP RIGHT AT
MEAL TIME, I PROBABLY AM A
LITTLE DISRUPTIVE TO THEM.
>> Jeff: HE THREW IT RIGHT
BACK AT YOU, KRISTINA.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE DOES.
I DO A LOT OF STUFF AROUND CAMP
TOO, JUST ABOUT AS MUCH AS YOU
DO, PHIL.
>> I WOULD BEG TO DIFFER.
>> ANYWAY, I DO A LOT OF STUFF,
TOO.
>> THE LAST THREE DAYS YOU HAVE,
YES.
>> Jeff: SO PHILLIP, CLEARLY,
YOU THINK IT SHOULD BE KRISTINA
TONIGHT.
KRISTINA, YOU CLEARLY THINK IT
SHOULD BE PHILLIP.
>> WELL, IF ME I HAVE A HISTORY
WITH THE TRIBE.
THEY KNOW WHAT I'M ABOUT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE A DOER.
>> IT'S WHAT I CALL THE SHEPPARD
STAMP.
AND THE SHEPPARD STAMP IS BEING
ONE OF 12, HAVING MY MOTHER PASS
AT A VERY EARLY AGE, AND HAVING
TO WORK MY WAY THROUGH HIGH
SCHOOL, DECIDING I WAS GOING TO
JOIN THE UNITED STATES ARMY AND
GETTING AN HONORABLE DISCHARGE,
RECEIVING THE SECOND HIGHEST
MEDAL YOU CAN GET DURING PEACE
TIME, DOING WHAT, FIELD
SANITATION?
WHAT A GLORIOUS JOB.
BUT I DID IT TO THE BEST OF MY
ABILITY.
AND THAT'S WHAT THESE GUYS SEE
OUT HERE EVERY SINGLE DAY.
SO I THINK BETWEEN KRISTINA AND
I, I THINK I'VE EARNED THE
RESPECT OF MY TRIBE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KRISTINA,
HE LAID OUT A VERY COMPELLING
ARGUMENT WHY THE TRIBE SHOULD
KEEP HIM.
BEFORE WE GO TO THE VOTE, YOUR
LAST CHANCE.
>> I DON'T THINK I HAD A CHANCE
AT THE VERY BEGINNING TO GET TO
KNOW EVERYONE BUT I'M A VALUABLE
MEMBER OF THIS TRIBE.
I'M SMART, AND I CAN BE TRUSTED
IN THIS TRIBE, AND I WANT TO
PROVE THAT TO THEM.
IF THEY'LL GIVE ME THAT
OPPORTUNITY, I CAN DO THAT.
>> Jeff: WE'RE GOING TO FIND
OUT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
NATALIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> KRISTINA, TIME HAS RUN OUT.
>> PHIL, YOU'RE A PAIN IN THE
NECK.
I REALLY HOPE IT'S YOU AND NOT
ME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, PHILLIP.
KRISTINA.
PHILLIP.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP.
KRISTINA.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP, TWO VOTES
KRISTINA.
PHILLIP.
THAT'S THREE VOTES PHILLIP, TWO
VOTES KRISTINA.
KRISTINA.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES PHILLIP, THREE VOTES
KRISTINA, ONE VOTE LEFT.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND."
KRISTINA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
KRISTINA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A SHOT TO GET BACK
IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WELL, RUNNING OUT OF TIME WAS
CLEARLY A THEME IN TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND IF YOU DON'T
START WINNING, TIME IS GOING TO
RUN OUT FOR THIS TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> YOU GOT YOUR UNDERWEAR ON?
>> I HAVE MY UNDERWEAR ON.
>> Jeff: SHIFTING ALLIANCES
CREATES STRANGE BEDFELLOWS.
>> PHILLIP IS BUGGING EVERYONE.
SO MAYBE HE NEEDS TO STAY.
>> Jeff: AND AT ZAPATERA
RUSSELL TAUGHT HIS GIRLS WELL.
>> WE'RE READY CAUSE SOME HAVOC
AND CHAOS.
>> Jeff: SO TRIBE UNITY
CRUMBLES.
>> DAVID IS STRESSFUL.
>> DON'T FREAK OUT.
>> THEY JUST GOT MY REAR END
RAKED ACROSS THE COALS AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T BE SURPRISED
BEING VOTED OFF OF "SURVIVOR"
BUT IT'S A WHOLE NEW BALLGAME
NOW.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO FACE OFF
WITH MATT AND DO THE BEST I CAN
AND GET OUT THERE AND GIVE IT
ALL I HAVE AND JUST ROCK IT.
THAT'S WHAT MY STRATEGY IS RIGHT
NOW.