>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
MATT, YOU ARE BACK
IN THIS GAME.
WE ARE MERGED.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
AT THE MERGE, MATT QUICKLY
REKINDLED HIS RELATIONSHIP
WITH ANDREA.
>> I'VE BEEN TALKING A LOT WITH
ANDREA BECAUSE I CONSIDER HER
MY CLOSEST ALLY.
>> Jeff: BUT ANDREA ANSWERED
TO A HIGHER POWER.
>> HERE'S WHAT'S GOING DOWN.
MATTY'S GOT TO GO HOME TONIGHT.
>> I REALLY LIKE MATT BUT ROB IS
KIND OF THE KING AROUND HERE.
I MEAN, HE'S VERY SMART.
>> Jeff: AND SHE JOINED HIM
IN HIS SECOND BLINDSIDE OF MATT.
MATT.
ONCE AGAIN,
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AT REDEMPTION ISLAND, IN THE
FIRST THREE-WAY DUEL,
MATT FACED DAVE AND MIKE.
MIKE AND MATT STAY ALIVE.
AND DAVE BECAME THE FIRST MEMBER
OF THE JURY.
BACK AT CAMP.
>> WE'RE GUARANTEED TO GO
TO THE FINAL SIX.
>> Jeff: THE FORMER
OMETEPE TRIBE
CELEBRATED THEIR NUMBERS
ADVANTAGE.
>> OMETEPE!
>> Jeff: BUT PHILLIP
BROKE UP THE PARTY
WHEN HE GOT INTO A
HEATED ARGUMENT WITH STEVE.
>> EVERY TIME I MAKE AN ARGUMENT
WITH ONE OF THOSE GUYS IT'S
I'M ( BLEEP ) CRAZY.
>> Jeff: AND STEVE'S ALLY
JULIE RETALIATED BY HIDING
PHILLIP'S SHORTS.
>> PHILLIP IS GOING TO HAVE TO
HANG OUT IN HIS UNDERWEAR
FROM NOW ON.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, IT
WAS CLEAR THE FORMER ZAPATERA
TRIBE WAS IN TROUBLE.
UNTIL PHILLIP DIRECTED
EVERYONE'S ATTENTION TO HIMSELF.
>> HE RESORTS
TO CALLING ME CRAZY
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T WANT
TO SAY THE "N" WORD.
HE WANTS TO SAY CRAZY,
CRAZY, CRAZY.
>> Jeff: AND JULIE SURPRISED
EVERYONE WHEN SHE CAME CLEAN.
>> I TOOK THE SHORTS.
NO ONE WILL EVER FIND THEM.
DUG A HOLE AND BURIED THEM
AND A ROCK WAS ON TOP OF THEM.
>> Jeff: BUT SHE GOT AN EVEN
BIGGER SURPRISE WHEN SHE WAS
SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
NOW RALPH AND STEVE
ARE ALL THAT REMAIN
OF THE FORMER ZAPATERA TRIBE,
AND THEIR ONLY HOPE,
A CRACK IN THE OMETEPE ALLIANCE.
>> YEAH.
>> I'D LIKE TO REACH OUT AN
OLIVE BRANCH HANDSHAKE TO YOU.
THERE ARE NO APOLOGIZES NEEDED
FROM EITHER ONE OF US.
YOU'RE A MAN. YOU HAD TO SAY
WHAT YOU HAD TO SAY.
>> AS SOON AS WE GOT
BACK TO CAMP
I WAS APPROACHED BY STEVE,
AND HE SAID,
"HEY, MAN,
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
I WANT TO BURY THE HATCHET.
I'M NOT A RACIST, MAN.
I'M REALLY NOT.
AND I HOPE WE CAN
GET TOGETHER ON IT,"
AND HE SHOOK MY HAND.
I DON'T FEEL IT WAS
TOTALLY GENUINE.
>> THERE WAS NO PREJUDICE
IN MY CRAZY COMMENT.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU WERE CRAZY.
>> OKAY, I HEAR YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT?
>> I FELT IT WAS A LITTLE
SELF-SERVING
BECAUSE HE MOCKED ME
A NUMBER OF TIMES,
AND SO PROBABLY STEVE
WILL GO NEXT.
PERFECT, I'M GLAD YOU CAME
AND SPOKE TO ME.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT, MAN.
>> YEAH.
I WOULD REALLY THINK
A MATURE GUY WITH ANY WISDOM
AND ANY EMPATHY
OR HEART OR WHATEVER
WOULD HAVE REACHED OUT AFTER
GOING OFF THE WAY HE DID,
BECAUSE HE HAD TO HAVE KNOWN,
YOU KNOW,
WHAT AN ASS HE MADE OF HIMSELF
BUT I WAS THE ONE WHO
REACHED OUT AND I THINK IT
HAD QUITE A BIT TO DO
WITH SETTLING
THE WHOLE RACE THING
HE BROUGHT UP
AND HOPEFULLY WE BURIED THAT.
>> GOOD BLINDSIDE TONIGHT, TOO.
>> OH, TONIGHT.
YOU GUYS DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING?
>> YOU DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING?
>> YEAH.
>> NO.
>> WE LIKE TO KEEP THINGS
INTERESTING.
>> YEAH, IT WILL MAKE OUR
REMAINING DAYS HERE
EASIER FOR EVERYBODY.
SO I'M JUST GOING TO KEEP
PLUGGING AWAY AND WORKING
THE RELATIONSHIPS
AND BEING OPEN
AND FRIENDLY AND WHO KNOWS?
BOSTON ROB MAY WANT TO JUST KEEP
MYSELF OR RALPH AROUND
AND MAYBE THEY'LL CUT
PHIL LOOSE.
>> I WAS NERVOUS.
I DIDN'T WANT TO SPEND
THAT MUCH TIME--
ON RACE AND I WAS LIKE,
OH, MY GOD!
>> PHILLIP IS NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
PHILLIP IS UNDER MY PROTECTION.
AS LONG AS HE KEEPS UP
HIS STUPID ANTICS,
THEY'LL BE COMING TO ME
ALL THE WAY TO THE FINALS.
>> THE LAST OF ZAPATERA MEN.
>> YUP.
>> WHERE'S NUMBNUTS?
>> HE WENT OUT THERE
TO THE BIG ROCK.
>> MAYBE HE'LL JUMP OFF.
>> YESTERDAY, MY TRUNKS
WERE HIDDEN BY JULIE
BEFORE SHE GOT VOTED OUT.
SO I GOT UP THIS MORNING,
AND I HAD A PREMONITION
THAT I WAS
GOING TO FIND MY SHORTS.
MY GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
FULL-BLOODED CHEROKEE INDIAN
CAME TO ME IN A VISION.
AND HE SAID,
"LOOK NEAR THE WATER HOLE."
I KNEW IT WASN'T THE OCEAN
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT,
IT WAS THE DRINKING WATER.
I WENT THERE, FOUND THE FIRST
ROCK, AND TURNED IT OVER.
NO, NOT THERE.
WENT TO THE SECOND ROCK,
THERE MY SHORTS WERE.
AM I GOOD OR WHAT?
AM I GOOD OR WHAT, BABY!
HE BE THE MAN!
HERE'S TO YOU, JULIE.
DON'T MESS WITH
THE UNDERCOVER SPECIALIST
BECAUSE HE MAKES HIS LIVING
UNCOVERING TRUTH,
AND MOST PEOPLE, LIKE YOU,
CAN'T STAND THE TRUTH.
WHAT DID JACK NICHOLSON SAY
TO TOM CRUISE?
"SON, YOU CAN'T STAND THE TRUTH.
YOU CAN'T TAKE THE TRUTH."
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING TO HER.
YOU CANNOT MESS
WITH THE SPECIALIST.
LET THIS BE WARNING TO ALL WHO
WOULD ATTEMPT TO HIDE
SOME SHORTS FROM ME.
IT'S FUTILE.
IT'S FRIVOLOUS.
BECAUSE WITHOUT A CLUE.
>> WHAT?
HOW DID YOU FIND THAT?
>> BABY, YOU KNOW,
I'M THE SPECIALIST.
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, BABY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
WE'RE AT PEACE NOW.
>> YOU BAD!
YOU BAD, BABY!
>> PHILLIP,
HE'S A DIFFERENT BREED.
AGAIN, THERE'S NO PREJUDICE
BEHIND IT, BUT HE'S
A LITTLE CRAZY.
IT'S-- IT'S CRAZY.
HEY!
>> HE'S A FREAKING LUNATIC.
I THINK THEY'RE GETTING
TIRED OF HIM, TOO.
>> I GOT SHORTS, BABY.
WOOO!
YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO
FIND THEM SHORTS,
AS SHE PARTED LAST NIGHT.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SHOW UP
WITH THEM TODAY.
>> WITH YOUR SHORTS ON.
>> YOU GOT IT.
NO CLUE, NOTHING.
>> SWEET.
>> YEAH.
I NEED TO GO GET THAT ROCK.
THAT BIG OLD ROCK
SHE TALKED ABOUT.
I AM SO EXCITED
ABOUT SEEING JULIE
AT THE DUEL TODAY
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO SHOW UP
IN THESE SHORTS.
MY NEW FOOTREST.
AND SHE'S GOING TO KNOW THAT YOU
CAN'T PULL THE WOOL OVER
THE UNDERCOVER SPECIALIST.
I AM TRULY BLESSED.
>> WERE YOU ABLE TO GET
SOME WINKS LAST NIGHT, JULIE?
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I SLEPT SO GOOD.
DAY WHAT, 28?
27 NIGHTS.
THAT WAS THE BEST NIGHT
I'VE EVER SLEPT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IT GETS HARDER AND HARD
TO GET UP EVERY MORNING.
MATT HAD INCREDIBLE STRENGTH
GOING THROUGH REDEMPTION ISLAND
THE FIRST TIME.
AFTER HE WAS BLINDSIDED
THE SECOND TIME
BY THE FOLKS HE THOUGHT
WERE TRULY HIS FRIENDS,
HE'S KIND OF BEEN ON
A LITTLE DOWNWARD SPIRAL.
>> I'M GONNA GO SIT ON THE BEACH
FOR LITTLE WHILE.
>> OKAY.
MATT HAS GREAT FAITH,
AND HE'S ABLE TO ENDURE
A LOT OF HARDSHIP
BECAUSE OF HIS FAITH IN GOD.
>> POOR MATT.
HE SEEMS LIKE HE'S DONE.
>> YEAH, HE'S PRETTY DOWN.
BUT YOU CAN TELL HE'S KIND OF
AT HIS BREAKING POINT.
YOU KNOW IT'S ALL THOSE
SUBCONSCIOUS THINGS.
HE'S ALREADY THINKING ABOUT
GOING HOME,
AND THAT CAN AFFECT
THE OUTCOME OF A CHALLENGE.
>> I THINK COMING BACK HERE WAS
REALLY, REALLY ROUGH ON HIM.
IT TOOK A LOT OF THE WIND
OUT OF HIS SAILS
AND AFTER BEING HERE
FOR THREE WEEKS AND COMPETING
IN, LIKE, SIX DUELS.
>> THIS IS UNLIKE ANYTHING I'VE
EVER REALLY EXPERIENCED.
I'M OUT HERE WASTING AWAY.
I'M MISSING MY FAMILY.
I CAN'T-- I CAN ONLY FEEL THEM
WHEN I REALLY, REALLY TRY.
>> I GUESS HE WAS REALLY CLOSE
TO ANDREA, TOO,
AND I GUESS SHE
WAS JUST SHARING EVERYTHING
THAT HE WAS TELLING HER.
>> I FIGURED.
>> WITH THE TRIBE.
>> I NEVER DID TRUST HER.
>> NO, SHE'S NOT TO BE TRUSTED.
>> GOD HAS ME HERE FOR A REASON.
I SAID THIS FROM THE BEGINNING
THAT GOD WANTED ME HERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE REASON IS FOR.
I CAN'T SEE THAT YET.
BUT I KNOW HE WANTS ME
TO BE HERE.
HE'S LITERALLY BEEN...
GOD HAS LITERALLY
BEEN CARRYING ME
FOR THE PAST FOUR DAYS.
I KNOW I'M STILL IN THE GAME BUT
I'M SO OVER THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS
FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
MATT, MIKE, AND JULIE.
MATT, 21 DAYS.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: ON REDEMPTION.
ONLY SEVEN DAYS IN THE REGULAR
GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
WHERE ARE YOU AT WITH THIS?
YOU'VE HAD AN INCREDIBLE
ROLLER COASTER
OF EMOTIONS OUT HERE.
>> JUST OVERWHELMING PEACE
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
I FELT THIS NEED
THAT IF I KEPT WINNING,
I COULD HONOR MY GOD
MORE AND MORE.
BUT HE JUST KIND OF HIT ME
WITH A LOT OF PEACE,
AND HE WAS JUST LIKE, YOU KNOW,
YOU'VE HONORED ME ENOUGH,
AND IF I GO BACK,
I GO BACK, AND IF I GO HOME,
THEN I GO HOME.
AND I'M AT PEACE WITH THAT.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A VERY
DIFFERENT MATT
THAN I'VE SEEN IN THE PAST.
IT SOUND TO ME LIKE
YOU'RE READY TO GO HOME.
>> UH, I'M GOING TO DO
THE BEST
I CAN IN TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
BUT, YEAH, I THINK
I'M READY TO GO HOME.
THE ONLY REASON I WAS STAYING
IN THIS GAME
IS BECAUSE I THOUGHT
THERE WAS MORE OF GOD'S WILL
TO ACCOMPLISH, AND I FEEL
LIKE I'VE ACCOMPLISHED
WHAT I CAME HERE TO DO.
SO WHATEVER HAPPENS,
I'M READY FOR IT.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET
TO TODAY'S DUEL.
IT IS "SURVIVOR" SHUFFLEBOARD.
YOU WILL EACH HAVE ONE
SHUFFLEBOARD AND THREE PUCKS.
YOUR GOAL-- SLIDE YOUR PUCK
ACROSS YOUR BOARD THROUGH THE
OBSTACLE, INTO THE END ZONE.
IF ANY PART OF YOUR PUCK TOUCHES
THE END ZONE, IT COUNTS.
THE FIRST TWO TO LAND ALL THREE
OF THEIR PUCKS IN THE END ZONE
STAY ALIVE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
LOSER IS OUT OF THIS GAME
FOR GOOD
AND WILL BECOME THE NEXT
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
CLEAR?
>> CLEAR.
>> Jeff: THIS IS MOST
DEFINITELY IT.
ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
MATT, YOU'RE UP
WITH THE FIRST SHOT.
THAT FIRST OBSTACLE, NO GOOD.
MIKE IS UP.
MIKE LANDS HIS FIRST PUCK
IN THE END ZONE.
JULIE'S UP.
JULIE SHORT.
WE'LL CLEAR THE PUCKS
EACH ROUND,
EXCEPT THE ONES
IN THE END ZONE.
THOSE WILL STAY.
KEEP YOUR BOARD CLEAN FOR YOU.
MIKE HAS ONE PUCK
IN THE END ZONE.
MATT AND JULIE ZERO.
MATT IS UP.
MATT SHORT AGAIN.
MIKE WITH ANOTHER NICE TOSS.
THAT IS IN THE END ZONE.
MIKE MAKING IT LOOK EASY.
HE HAS TWO OF HIS PUCKS
IN THE END ZONE.
JULIE, YOU'RE UP.
JULIE LANDS ONE IN THE END ZONE.
JULIE WITH HER FIRST PUCK.
MATT, YOU'VE GOT TO GET
ON THE BOARD.
>> I'M WORKING ON IT.
>> Jeff: MATT LANDS ONE
IN THE END ZONE,
JUST BARELY,
BUT THAT WILL COUNT.
>> MATT'S KIND OF PISSED AT ME.
I MADE EYE CONTACT KIND OF, AND
IT ALMOST LOOKED LIKE HE GAVE ME
A REALLY DIRTY LOOK.
I COULD HAVE BEEN READING
INTO IT,
BUT IT WAS JUST, LIKE,
A WEIRD FEELING.
>> Jeff: MIKE COULD STAY ALIVE
ON REDEMPTION WITH THIS SHOT
RIGHT HERE.
NOPE.
JULIE SHORT.
MATT LOOKING
FOR THAT SECOND PUCK.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
MATT NOW WITH TWO PUCKS.
ALL IT TAKES IS THREE
TO STAY ALIVE.
MIKE IS SHORT.
JULIE LOOKING TO LAND
THAT SECOND PUCK AND STAY EVEN.
SHORT AGAIN.
MATT, YOU'RE UP.
GOD IS NOT DONE TALKING TO MATT.
MATT HAS THREE PUCKS
IN THE END ZONE.
YOU ARE STAYING ALIVE
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WHETHER YOU WANT
TO BE HERE OR NOT.
HERE'S WHERE WE STAND--
TWO PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO STAY ALIVE ON REDEMPTION.
ONE IS OUT OF THIS GAME
FOR GOOD.
MIKE HAS TWO PUCKS
IN THE END ZONE.
JULIE HAS ONLY ONE.
MIKE COULD DO IT RIGHT HERE
WITH THIS SHOT.
CAN HE DO IT?
OH!
>> OH!
>> Jeff: JUST SHORT.
LESS THAN A QUARTER OF AN INCH.
JULIE STAYS ALIVE.
>> COME ON, JULIE.
>> Jeff: JULIE, GOTTA LAND THIS.
JULIE LANDS ONE IN THE END ZONE
BUT KNOCKS ANOTHER ONE OUT.
JULIE STAYS RIGHT WHERE SHE WAS
WITH ONLY ONE PUCK
IN THE END ZONE.
MIKE COULD DO IT RIGHT HERE.
AND HE DOES!
MIKE AND MATT STAY ALIVE
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> IT WAS MEANT TO BE.
GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: SO, MATT,
ARE YOU FRUSTRATED
WITH YOUR GOD RIGHT NOW?
>> I MEAN, YOU JUST GOTTA
BE ACCEPTING.
I GUESS HE STILL WANTS ME HERE
FOR SOME REASON.
I TOLD HIM I'D STAY HERE
AS LONG AS HE WANTED TO.
>> Jeff: HOW MANY DAYS
DID JESUS FAST?
>> 40.
>> Jeff: IT'S INTERESTING
OUR GAME IS 39 DAYS.
DOING WELL SO FAR.
JULIE, AFTER 28 DAYS.
>> 28 DAYS, YEAH,
OF NOT BRUSHING YOUR TEETH.
HOLY MOLY.
>> Jeff: WHY WERE YOU OUT HERE?
>> I DIDN'T COME OUT HERE
TO MAKE FRIENDS.
LIKE MANY AMERICANS,
MY HOUSE IS IN FORECLOSURE,
AND THIS WAS AN OPPORTUNITY
FOR ME TO MAKE
A BETTER LIFE FOR MY GIRLS.
AND MY KIDS ARE PROUD OF ME
EITHER WAY, YOU KNOW.
AND I CAME SHORT OF THE MONEY,
BUT I'M WALKING AWAY
WITH SOMETHING BIGGER.
MY LIFE IS-- IS CHANGED.
I SEE MATT'S STORY WITH GOD,
AND I AM LOOKING FORWARD
TO GOING BACK HOME,
FINDING A CHURCH,
AND JUST GETTING INVOLVED.
>> Jeff: JULIE, YOUR SHOT
AT THE MONEY IS OVER.
YOU ARE OUT OF THIS GAME.
YOU CAN TOSS YOUR BUFF
IN THE URN ON THE WAY OUT.
BUT YOU'RE NOT LEAVING US.
YOU'RE GOING TO RETURN AND BE
A SECOND MEMBER OF THE JURY.
>> WAY TO GO, JULEZ.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS.
( APPLAUSE )
GOOD LUCK.
>> PEANUT BUTTER AND OATMEAL!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
YOU BOTH STAY ALIVE
TO LIVE ANOTHER DAY
ON REDEMPTION.
NICE WORK.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> HANG IN THERE, MATT.
>> I HOPE THAT MATT STAYS,
AND MAYBE HE CAN COME BACK.
AND, LIKE, IF HE CAME BACK
IN THE GAME,
I'D, LIKE, WANT TO TALK TO HIM
BUT I DON'T THINK
HE CAN REALLY TRUST ME,
LIKE, IN THIS GAME EVER AGAIN.
WHY WOULD HE?
>> IT FELT WEIRD.
LIKE, I FELT, LIKE, REALLY BAD
ABOUT MYSELF FOR, LIKE,
PLAYING HIM.
YOU KNOW, FOR ALL OF US
>> NO--
>> I DID.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE WANTED.
LIKE, HE DIDN'T WANT
TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> LIKE HIS SPIRIT
SEEMED BROKEN.
I DON'T KNOW, IT WAS WEIRD.
IT WAS JUST, LIKE
A WEIRD FEELING.
MATT WAS LIKE, I DON'T CARE
IF I GO OUT.
I FEEL BAD BECAUSE I PLAYED HIM
THE HARDEST.
I HAD CLOSE CONVERSATIONS
WITH HIM
AND HE SAID HE FORGIVES US
ALL AND STUFF
BUT I THINK HE'S
KIND OF PISSED AT ME.
>> WE ALL PUT HIM THERE,
YOU KNOW.
>> UH-HUH.
>> IT WASN'T JUST YOU.
>> NO, I KNOW.
I JUST--
>> YEAH--
>> I DEFINITELY PLAYED HIM
THE HARDEST.
I FEEL LIKE I WAS A BIG PART OF,
LIKE, BREAKING HIS SPIRIT.
SO IN A WAY I KIND OF, LIKE,
FELT A LITTLE GUILTY
ON A HUMAN LEVEL,
NOT ON A GAME LEVEL.
>> I WAS THINKING
THE SAME THING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
BECAUSE, ONE, SHE IS PRETTY GOOD
IN CHALLENGES,
AS FAR AS PUZZLES AND STUFF GO.
BUT WE DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT--
>> AND SHE'S, LIKE, FRIENDS
WITH WITH ALL THE OTHER PEOPLE
OVER THERE,
AND SHE'S HAVING
SECOND THOUGHTS.
>> I THINK, DUDE,
THE FIRST CHANCE WE GET,
GET HER OUT OF THERE.
I'VE BEEN CONCERNED ABOUT ANDREA
AND MATT'S RELATIONSHIP.
IF HE COMES BACK
FROM REDEMPTION ISLAND,
WE GOT BACK FROM THE CHALLENGE,
AND SHE SAID SHE FELT
SORRY FOR HIM.
IT'S THINGS LIKE THAT JUST--
YOU'RE KIND OF SHAKING
YOUR HEAD GOING,
AH, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'VE LEARNED.
IF WE PLAY THIS RIGHT,
IT SHOULD BE SMOOTH SAILING.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> WE DECIDE WHO GOES WHEN,
AND THAT'S IT.
>> THE UPSIDE
TO GETTING RID OF ANDREA
BEFORE GETTING RID OF STEVE
AND RALPH
BECAUSE THAT'S ONE
LESS THING TO WORRY ABOUT.
THEN AGAIN, TIMING
IS EVERYTHING IN THIS GAME.
WHEN TO PULL THE TRIGGER
AS FAR AS WHEN
TO VOTE PEOPLE OFF IS HUGE.
AND IT MIGHT COME DOWN TO JUST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, YOU KNOW.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
BOSTON ROB, GIVE IT UP.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
IN TODAY'S CHALLENGE,
YOU WILL COMPETE IN A LOG ROLL.
YOU WILL MATCH UP AGAINST
ANOTHER TRIBEMEMBER.
YOUR GOAL-- STAY ON THE LOG
LONGER THAN THE OTHER PERSON.
FIRST PERSON TO HIT THE WATER
IS OUT, WINNERS MOVE ON.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING
WINS IMMUNITY, IS SAFE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION TODAY,
YOU ARE PLAYING FOR REWARD.
AFTER 30 DAYS, I CAN'T IMAGINE
ANYBODY THAT DOESN'T HAVE
A SWEET TOOTH.
>> OH!
>> MY GOD!
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I ASKED FOR.
>> Jeff: CHOCOLATE CAKE.
AND, OF COURSE, ICE COLD MILK.
>> OH!
>> OH, MAN!
>> Jeff: IN ADDITION TODAY,
ONE OTHER TWIST, WHICH I WILL
TELL YOU ABOUT LATER.
I KNOW IT'S WORTH PLAYING FOR.
WE'LL DRAW FOR MATCH-UPS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
OUR FIRST MATCH-UP,
GRANT TAKING ON BOSTON ROB.
FIRST ONE TO HIT THE WATER
IS OUT.
THE WINNER MOVES ON.
MOVE ON OUT TO THE COLOR.
WE'RE ON.
GOOD FIRST MATCH.
ROB IS IN THE WATER FIRST.
GRANT WINS AND MOVES ON.
>> I LOVE YOU, ROB.
>> Jeff: NEXT TWO, IT IS
ANDREA TAKING ON ASHLEY.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
ANDREA'S IN THE WATER FIRST.
ASHLEY MOVES ON.
NEXT MATCH-UP,
RALPH TAKING ON STEVE.
STEVE, HAVE YOU EVER DONE
ANYTHING LIKE THIS?
>> YEAH, I'M IN A LEAGUE,
A LEAGUE EVERY SATURDAY.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
GOOD FOOTWORK.
STEVE IS IN FIRST.
RALPH MOVES ON.
LAST MATCH-UP
IN THIS FIRST ROUND.
NATALIE TAKING ON PHILLIP.
WE'RE ON.
NATALIE IS IN FIRST.
PHILLIP MOVES ON.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT ROUND.
IT IS GRANT TAKING ON ASHLEY.
THE WINNER OF THIS MATCH
MOVES ON TO THE FINAL ROUND.
HERE WE GO.
GRANT TRYING
TO GET ASHLEY RUNNING.
NICE RECOVERY.
ASHLEY IN THE WATER.
GRANT MOVING ON TO THE FINAL!
NEXT ROUND IT IS RALPH
TAKING ON PHILLIP.
WINNER OF THIS MOVES ON
INTO THE FINAL
WHERE THEY WILL MATCH UP
AGAINST GRANT.
WE'RE GOOD.
>> COME ON, PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: NICE, NICE RECOVERY.
PHILLIP IS IN FIRST.
RALPH MOVES ON TO THE FINAL
AGAINST GRANT.
>> WAY TO GO, RALPHY.
>> Jeff: THIS IS IT,
THE FINAL ROUND.
GRANT TAKING ON RALPH.
IMMUNITY, CHOCOLATE CAKE
FOR THE WINNER.
THIS IS IT.
GRANT AND RALPH.
>> LET'S GO, BIG COUNTRY.
>> GOOD JOB, GRANT.
>> Jeff: GOT A GOOD MATCH GOING.
NICE RECOVERY.
ANOTHER NICE RECOVERY.
>> LET'S GO, RALPH.
>> Jeff: BOTH GUYS LOOKING
PRETTY COMFORTABLE.
WHO'S GOING IN FIRST?
RALPH IS IN, GRANT WINS IMMUNITY
AND CHOCOLATE CAKE!
>> YEAH, GRANT!
>> GRANT!
>> Jeff: GRANT, NICE WORK.
GRANT SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, YOU'VE WON
A HUGE CHOCOLATE CAKE.
>> IT IS PRETTY BIG.
>> Jeff: IT IS PRETTY BIG,
AND I KNOW
EVEN AFTER A MONTH
AND A MOUTH FULL OF SWEET TEETH
YOU COULDN'T EAT
THAT CAKE ALONE.
>> I COULDN'T.
>> Jeff: CHOOSE ONE PERSON
TO JOIN YOU.
>> GUYS, I'M SORRY, I GOTTA--
ROB, COME ON DOWN.
( APPLAUSE )
>> I WISH EVERYBODY
COULD HAVE SOME.
I'M SORRY.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GRANT,
CHOOSE ONE MORE PERSON
TO EAT WITH YOU.
>> MAN, I'D HUG YOUR NECK
IF YOU'D LET ME
EAT SOME OF THAT.
>> Jeff: THAT MAY JUST PUT YOU
OUT OF THE RUNNING.
>> I'M NOT A GAY PERSON,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GRANT,
ONE MORE CHOICE.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> AH...
ANDREA, COME ON DOWN.
I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS.
I'M SORRY!
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
AND THE TWIST THAT I
REFERRED TO EARLIER.
DO NOT OPEN THAT.
IT IS FOR THE TRIBE.
BRING IT WITH YOU TONIGHT
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO ROB,
ANDREA, AND GRANT
ARE GOING TO FEAST
ON CHOCOLATE CAKE.
YOU WILL HAVE TWO MINUTES
TO EAT AS MUCH AS YOU CAN.
THE TWO MINUTES START NOW.
>> JUST EAT IT LIKE A PIG.
>> I DON'T WANT TO CHOKE.
>> THERE IS SO MUCH
RICH FUDGE IN THERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I WISH EVERYBODY
COULD HAVE SOME.
>> DON'T TALK.
JUST EAT.
>> I CHOSE ANDREA
AS A STRATEGIC MOVE
OF WANTING TO MAKE HER FEEL
COMFORTABLE IN OUR ALLIANCE,
BECAUSE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL,
IF CERTAIN SCENARIOS COME UP,
WHERE WE NEED TO GET RID
OF ONE OF OUR OWN,
ANDREA IS GOING TO BE
THAT MEMBER.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GOOD!
>> WE GOT A MYSTERY PACKAGE.
JEFF GAVE IT TO US AND SAID WE
HAD TO OPEN IT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT COULD BE SOMETHING WHERE WE--
YOU KNOW, WE GO, WE VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND THE TWIST IS WE VOTE
ANOTHER PERSON OUT,
OR SOMETHING LIKE
CRAZY OUTLANDISH.
>> WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK
THE TWIST IS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT FEELS LIKE A DECK
OF CARDS, HUH?
>> LIKE IF YOU PICK THE WRONG
CARD YOU'RE GOING HOME?
>> MAYBE.
>> THE WHOLE CARD THING
KIND OF THREW ME OFF
BUT RIGHT NOW
EVERYBODY FEELS COMFORTABLE
BECAUSE THERE ARE THE TWO EASY
VOTES, RALPH AND STEVE.
>> I'M BEAT, MAN.
>> I THINK THAT US SIX HAVING
SO MUCH FAITH IN EACH OTHER,
I THINK IT WOULD BE SILLY
TO GET RID
OF ONE OF OUR OWN
BEFORE THE ZAPATERA PEOPLE.
>> PARDON ME?
>> ONE MORE TIME.
>> CAN'T PULL ANOTHER WIN.
I'M DISAPPOINTED IN MYSELF.
I THOUGHT I COULD DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
GAVE IT ALL I HAD.
ONE OF US IS ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK,
AND IT'S PROBABLY ME.
ALL I CAN DO IS HOPE
WHATEVER IS IN THAT LITTLE BOX
THAT JEFF SAID
TO DEFINITELY BRING
IS GOOD NEWS FOR ME.
IT MIGHT NOT BE.
CHANCES IT BEING FOR ME, NO,
BUT ALL I'M DOING IS HOPING.
ALL I CAN DO IS HOPE.
>> THOSE CARDS WILL STIR UP
SOMETHING TONIGHT.
ME, I'M READY TO DROP.
MY STRENGTH IS-- IS--
MY STOMACH IS JUST SUCKED IN.
>> THIS IS WHAT'S GOING ON
RIGHT NOW--
STEVE'S THINKING, I'VE HAD IT.
I'M DONE.
SO STEVE'S NOT
GOING TO DO ANYTHING
TO CAUSE ANY PROBLEMS
WITH ANYBODY.
RALPH, ON THE OTHER HAND,
POSES A THREAT
BECAUSE PHYSICALLY,
HE'S CAPABLE AND HIS HEAD
IS STILL IN THE GAME
SO RALPH'S GOT TO GO NEXT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY THERE
HAS TO BE A TWIST.
ALWAYS A TWIST.
>> I'M ACTUALLY EXCITED
ABOUT THE TWIST.
>> I AM, TOO, BECAUSE
THE BALL'S IN OUR COURT.
>> WHO KNOWS WHAT THIS TWIST
IS ALL ABOUT.
MAYBE SOMEBODY ELSE HAS
A CHANCE TO WIN IMMUNITY.
MAYBE IT'S A SITUATION
WHERE TWO PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO GO HOME
BUT WE ONLY GET TO VOTE ONCE.
IT COULD BE ANYTHING.
SO WE'VE GOT TO HEDGE OUR BETS
AND MAKE SURE WE HAVE
BACKUP PLANS
AND KNOW WHO WE'RE VOTING FOR.
GRANT AND I, WE ALREADY TALKED
ABOUT GETTING RID OF ANDREA
BEFORE ZAPATERA,
SO IT LEAVES US OTHER OPTIONS.
>> TONIGHT,
IT'S OBVIOUSLY RALPH.
IF IT'S A TWIST AND WE HAVE
TO GET RID OF TWO PEOPLE--
>> IF WE HAVE TO VOTE
SOMEBODY ELSE OFF.
>> THEN IT'S HER.
>> ROB'S VERY SMART, AND HE'S
PLAYED THIS GAME BEFORE, AND SO
WE'RE KIND OF TAKING
OUR LEAD FROM HIM.
WE'RE VOTING FOR RALPH TONIGHT.
THERE'S ALSO A TWIST, THOUGH,
AND WE MAY HAVE TO VOTE OUT
TWO PEOPLE TONIGHT,
IN WHICH CASE,
ANDREA WILL GO HOME.
IF MATT COMES BACK
FROM REDEMPTION ISLAND,
SHE'S STILL GOT
A SOFT SPOT FOR MATT,
SO IT JUST MAKES SENSE
TO GET HER OUT.
YOU THREE GIRLS COULD TURN THIS
WHOLE THING UPSIDE DOWN.
I WOULD GUARANTEE YOU THAT ROB'S
PRETTY MUCH MAKING THE DECISIONS
WHO COMES AND WHO GOES.
HE'LL START PICKING
YOU GUYS OFF,
AND TAKE NIMROD WITH HIM
TO THE FINALS.
NOBODY WILL VOTE FOR NIMROD.
SO WE'RE DEFINITELY GOING TO BE
VOTING FOR ROB TONIGHT.
IF YOU THREE JUMP IN,
IT'S YOUR GAME.
>> WE'LL CONSIDER.
THANK YOU.
>> STEVE CAME UP TO US
AND WAS BASICALLY LIKE
OUR TWO VOTES ARE GOING FOR ROB,
SO IF YOU THREE GIRLS
WANT TO MAKE A BIG MOVE,
LIKE, NOW'S THE TIME,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
WHICH, OBVIOUSLY,
WE DIDN'T ENTERTAIN.
>> I KNEW THEY WERE
GOING TO DO THIS.
IT'S THEIR LAST ATTEMPT,
AND THAT'S WHY
THEY'RE JUST TRYING
TO GET ANYTHING THEY CAN
AND DO WHATEVER THEY CAN.
SO LET'S JUST HANG IN THERE.
>> YEAH.
>> IT SEEMED LIKE STEVE MAY HAVE
GOTTEN HIS SECOND WIND.
HE'S GOING TO MEMBERS OF MY
ALLIANCE BEHIND MY BACK
TRYING TO COME UP WITH A PLAN
TO GET ME OUT OF HERE,
WHICH MAKES ME THINK I SHOULD
MAYBE GET RID OF HIM FIRST.
WHAT I WAS ORIGINALLY
THINKING ABOUT
I'M THINKING ABOUT NOT DOING NOW
BECAUSE I MAY HAVE TO WAIT
TO GET RID OF ANDREA.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
DAVID AND JULIE.
ROB, THE LAST THREE
TRIBAL COUNCILS,
ZAPATERA, ZAPATERA, ZAPATERA.
IS THAT WHERE WE ARE AGAIN?
IS IT GOING TO BE STEVE
OR RALPH?
>> MOST LIKELY.
UNLESS THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
>> Jeff: STEVE,
YOU KIND OF SENSE THAT,
THAT THIS OMETEPE GROUP
IS UNBREAKABLE?
>> SURE, YEAH,
THE WRITING'S ON THE WALL.
WE'VE TRIED TO STIR IT UP
AND RAISE A LITTLE HAVOC.
WE'VE TOLD VARIOUS GROUPS
WHO RALPH AND I ARE VOTING FOR,
AND IF THEY WANT
TO JUMP ON BOARD,
IT COULD BE HUGE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, STEVE DOES
MAKE A GOOD POINT.
AT MOST, THE OMETEPE SIX
HAVE TWO MORE VOTES.
STEVE AND RALPH.
THERE IS A CERTAIN TIME WHEN IT
MIGHT MAKE SENSE
TO SAY I'M MAKING A MOVE.
>> I MEAN, IT DOES MAKE SENSE
STRATEGICALLY,
BUT I FEEL COMPLETELY SAFE
THAT WE'RE ALL ROCK SOLID
BECAUSE WE REALLY DO
FEEL LIKE WE'VE WORKED HARD
TO GET TO THE PLACE
THAT WE'RE AT.
>> Jeff: RALPH, ODDS ARE,
TONIGHT'S VOTE,
ONE OF YOU TWO ARE GOING HOME.
>> WELL, I WENT A LITTLE FURTHER
IN THE GAME TONIGHT.
I'D SAY IT'S GOING TO BE ME.
>> Jeff: STEVE, HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> I'M THINKING IT MOST LIKELY
WOULD BE RALPH.
RALPH'S BEEN REALLY TOUGH
IN THE CHALLENGES.
BETTER PERFORMING THAN MYSELF.
SO...
>> Jeff: ROB, THAT'S THE RIGHT
THING TO SAY IF YOU'RE STEVE.
"I DON'T HAVE MUCH ENERGY.
I'M KIND OF WORTHLESS
IN CHALLENGES.
VOTE HIM OUT."
>> IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO SAY
IF HE WANTS TO STAY.
>> UH-HUH.
>> BUT, JEFF,
YOU CAN'T TAKE STEVE'S
LACKADAISICAL ANSWER
AS "I'M QUITTING."
THE DUDE PLAYED IN THE NFL.
HE'S NOT QUITTING.
>> Jeff: NOT A QUITTER.
>> HE'S NOT A QUITTER.
>> I WOULD SECOND
WHAT GRANT JUST SAID
BECAUSE I'M RECOGNIZING
THAT HE'S NOT AS FEEBLE
AS BEING PUT OUT THERE.
I THINK HE COULD STEP UP
AT THE RIGHT CHALLENGE.
GOTCHA.
>> Jeff: STEVE,
BEFORE WE GO TO THE VOTE,
THIS COULD BE
YOUR LAST CHANCE TO SPEAK UP.
>> I REMIND THE GIRLS
OF THE SEASONS PAST,
BOSTON ROB ASKED A GUY
TO SAVE HIS GIRLFRIEND,
AMBER, THEN CUT HIM LOOSE
THE FIRST CHANCE HE HAD.
SO IT WILL GET BRUTAL
AFTER RALPH AND I ARE GONE.
SO IT'S NOW OR NEVER
TO DO SOMETHING LARGE.
>> Jeff: STEVE IS BRINGING UP
"SURVIVOR: ALL-STARS"
IN WHICH IF YOU'RE
A "SURVIVOR" FAN YOU KNOW
ROB MADE AN ALLIANCE WITH AMBER
ALL THE WAY TO THE END
AND SHE BEAT HIM.
THERE WAS ONE CRITICAL MOMENT
WHERE HE NEEDED HELP
FROM SOMEBODY
AND AFTER HE GOT HIS HELP,
HE CUT HIS THROAT.
THE OTHER SIDE OF THE COIN
IS HE DIDN'T BETRAY AMBER.
IN FACT, HE HASN'T
BETRAYED HER SINCE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
YOU CAN LOOK AT THE FLIP SIDE
IF YOU HAVE
A GOOD RELATIONSHIP WITH ROB
AND HE GIVES YOU HIS WORD,
HE COULD TAKE YOU ALL THE WAY.
>> Jeff: HARD TO DENY HISTORY.
YOU BETRAYED LEX,
BUT YOU STAYED TRUE
TO THE TRUE ALLIANCE WITH AMBER.
>> THE ONE I STILL HAVE
TO THIS DAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
GRANT HAS THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
CANNOT VOTE FOR GRANT.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
GRANT, YOU'RE UP.
>> LET'S DO IT!
LET'S DO IT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU'D LIKE TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ROB.
ROB.
TWO VOTES ROB.
RALPH.
THAT'S THREE VOTES RALPH.
FOUR VOTE RALPH.
TWO VOTES ROB.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT.
RALPH. THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
RALPH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> SEE YOU, JEFF.
>> Jeff: NOT SO FAST.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU'RE STILL IN THIS GAME.
OKAY, NOW LET'S GET TO THE TWIST
I MENTIONED
AT THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
WHO HAS IT?
OPEN IT UP.
FLIP OVER THAT TOP CARD
AND READ THE BACK OF IT.
>> THIS COULD BE INTERESTING.
>> "YOU WILL NOW COMPETE IN YOUR
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
YOU WILL THEN
IMMEDIATELY VOTE OUT
ONE MORE TRIBE MEMBER."
>> "YOU WILL NOW COMPETE IN YOUR
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
YOU WILL THEN
IMMEDIATELY VOTE OUT
ONE MORE TRIBE MEMBER."
>> Jeff: STEVE, YOU CAN HOLD
ON TO THOSE CARS.
I'M GOING TO GIVE A STACK
OF CARDS TO EVERYBODY ELSE,
AND GRAB THE NECKLACE FROM YOU,
GRANT.
>> STEVE'S GOTTA WIN.
>> Jeff: TAKE A LOOK
THROUGH THOSE CARDS,
GET FAMILIAR WITH THEM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING TO WORK.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU GUYS
A SERIES OF SYMBOLS.
YOU'RE GOING TO REPEAT THEM
BACK TO ME
USING THE SYMBOLS ON YOUR CARD.
EVERY TIME YOU GET IT RIGHT,
YOU STAY ALIVE.
IF YOU MISS ONE, YOU ARE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT
IN THIS CHALLENGE
WINS IMMUNITY,
IS SAFE AT THE VOTE
THAT WILL HAPPEN IMMEDIATELY
FOLLOWING THIS CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
SHOW ME THE FIRST SYMBOL
I SHOWED YOU.
EVERYBODY HAS THE CANTEEN.
THE CANTEEN IS RIGHT.
SHOW ME THE SECOND SYMBOL
I SHOWED YOU.
HOOK WAS THE SECOND SYMBOL.
EVERYBODY IS STILL ALIVE.
SHOW ME THE THIRD SYMBOL.
WHAT WAS THE THIRD SYMBOL
THAT I SHOWED YOU?
NATALIE IS NOT SURE.
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
EVERYBODY HAS THE POT.
EVERYBODY'S RIGHT.
NATALIE, YOU'RE STILL
NOT SURE YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE FOURTH SYMBOL I SHOWED YOU.
STEVE, ROB, ANDREA, GRANT,
AND ASHLEY ALL HAVE FIRE.
PHILLIP HAS THE KNIFE.
NATALIE HAS THE MACHETE.
CORRECT ANSWER--
>> AAH!
>> Jeff: FIRE.
NATALIE IS OUT
AND PHILLIP IS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
WHAT'S THE NEXT SYMBOL
I SHOWED YOU?
STEVE SHOWS CANTEEN.
ASHLEY SHOWS CANTEEN.
ROB SHOWS CANTEEN.
GRANT AND ANDREA SHOW POT.
THE CORRECT SYMBOL WAS CANTEEN.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: GRANT AND ANDREA
ARE OUT OF IT.
WE ARE DOWN TO ASHLEY,
ROB, AND STEVE.
ALL RIGHT, SHOW ME
THE NEXT SYMBOL.
ASHLEY AND STEVE SHOW FIRE.
ROB SHOWS POT.
THE CORRECT SYMBOL WAS POT.
ROB WINS IMMUNITY.
NICE JOB, MARIANO.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO GO
STRAIGHT INTO THE VOTE.
ROB HAS IMMUNITY.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR ROB.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
NATALIE, IF YOU'LL COME
GET THE URN.
>> OMETEPE!
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS
THE HIDDEN EMIMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTE ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, GRANT.
STEVE.
TWO VOTES STEVE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES STEVE.
ONE VOTE GRANT.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT.
STEVE.
THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
STEVE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
THERE ARE NO MORE
ZAPATERAS LEFT.
THAT'S THE GOOD NEWS.
BAD NEWS-- NOWHERE LEFT TO HIDE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
FOR 30 DAYS, THE OMETEPE SIX
HAVE DOMINATED THE GAME.
>> OMETEPE!
>> Jeff: BUT NOW THEY'RE
FORCED TO TURN ON EACH OTHER.
>> ONE OF US HAS TO GO
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THAT'S A FACT.
>> Jeff: AND A MASSIVE CHALLENGE
LEAVES EVERYONE DEPLETED.
>> 32 DAYS OF HARD WORK
GONE JUST LIKE THAT.
>> I SEE DAYLIGHT AHEAD NOW.
IF ONE OF US ZAPATERA GUYS
GETS INTO THE TOP THREE,
WE'LL BE THE ONE TO WIN IT.
I WANT TO BE THAT GUY.
I BET YOU STEVE LOST 40 POUNDS.
>> 40 POUNDS, PROBABLY.
>> I MEAN, HE'S PITIFUL.
>> YOU GOT ROOM FOR ONE MORE?
STEVE! STEVE!