>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": 18 PEOPLE
BEGAN THE GAME.
TWO PLAYED BEFORE, BOSTON ROB
AND RUSSELL HANTZ.
TOGETHER THESE TWO OFFER 156
DAYS OF "SURVIVOR "EXPERIENCE.
THERE'S A NEW TWIST:
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU'RE SENT HERE WHEN YOU'RE
VOTED OUT.
FRANCESCA WAS FIRST.
SHE WAS MISERABLE.
>> OH! GOD.
>> Jeff: LIVING ALONE, WAITING
FOR THE NEXT PERSON TO ARRIVE.
AT THE ZAPATERA TRIBE, RUSSELL
TOLD EVERYONE THAT HE HAD
CHANGED.
>> I'M NOT HERE TO SABOTAGE
ANYTHING FROM NOBODY.
>> Jeff: HE LIED.
>> I HAVE TO BUILD TRUST WITH
THESE GUYS FOR ME TO STAB THEM
IN THE BACK.
>> Jeff: THEN HE MADE AN
ALLIANCE WITH THE TWO YOUNGEST
WOMEN ON THE BEACH.
>> KRISTA AND STEFANIE ARE MY
TWO GIRLS.
>> Jeff: AND WENT HUNTING FOR
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL,
BUT IT WAS RALPH WHO FOUND IT.
>> RUSSELL, EAT YOUR HEART OUT,
MAN.
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA WINS IMMUNITY!
DESPITE THE LOSS, ROB WAS STILL
IN CONTROL.
>> IT IS UNBELIEVABLE HOW WELL
HE CAN PLAY THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: BUT THEN, ROB TOOK HIS
GAME TO AN EVEN HIGHER LEVEL.
>> THE WHEELS ARE IN MOTION FOR
EVERYTHING TO HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: SO HE CONVINCED PHILLIP
TO BE A DECOY AND PRETEND HE WAS
BEING VOTED OUT.
>> YOU'RE AN ACTOR, BRO.
YOU NEED TO FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
GOING HOME.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: AND HE LET KRISTINA
THINK IF SHE DIDN'T PLAY HER
IMMUNITY IDOL, SHE WOULD GO
HOME.
>> I'M PLAYING IT FOR SURE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
EVERYTHING WENT AS PLANNED.
>> JEFF, I THINK I'M GOING TO
NEED A LITTLE EXTRA HELP
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALLOWING ROB TO BREAK
UP A POTENTIALLY POWERFUL
ALLIANCE BETWEEN ANDREA AND
MATT.
MATT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
MATT WAS COMPLETELY BLINDSIDED.
NOW HE HEADS TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND TO TAKE ON FRANCESCA IN A
DUEL, LEAVING ANDREA WONDERING
WHERE SHE STANDS WITH ROB.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> MATT?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M SHOCKED.
>> YEAH, I AM, TOO.
A LITTLE SHOCKED.
>> WOW.
WAIT A SECOND.
WHY ARE YOU HERE INSTEAD OF
PHILLIP?
>> WELL, THAT'S... THAT'S AN
EXCELLENT QUESTION.
>> WOW. SO MATT GOT BLINDSIDED.
I THOUGHT THAT SEEING ANY PART
OF ROB'S ALLIANCE TONIGHT WAS AN
IMPOSSIBILITY.
SO I JUST KNEW IT WOULD BE
PHILLIP.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY OF MY STUFF
AT ALL.
I WAS COMPLETELY BLINDSIDED.
>> HE'S A...
>> SCOUNDREL.
>> UH-HUH.
>> YEAH.
I FEEL SICK TO MY STOMACH RIGHT
NOW.
LIKE, IT REALLY... IT REALLY
HURTS.
I MEAN, THERE'S A LITTLE ANGER.
I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS I JUST
TRUSTED BOSTON TOO SOON.
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A GOOBER NOW
BECAUSE I LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT.
EVERYTHING WAS GREAT AT CAMP.
EVERYONE WAS GETTING ALONG AND
THEN WAAH.
THIS IS BRUTAL.
IT'S DEFINITELY HARD TO COME
HERE AND PICK YOURSELF UP AFTER
YOU'VE BEEN AS BLINDSIDED AS I
WAS.
AT THE SAME TIME, WHAT AN
OPPORTUNITY.
TO BE THE UNDERDOG AND COME BACK
FROM REDEMPTION ISLAND AND
FINISH THIS GAME WITH A MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> HOW GOOD DID THAT WORK OUT
TONIGHT?
>> TONIGHT COULD NOT HAVE GONE
ANY BETTER.
NOT ONLY DO WE BLINDSIDE MATT.
WE WERE ABLE TO HAVE KRISTINA
GET RID OF HER IMMUNITY IDOL,
AND PHILLIP WAS A LOYAL SOLDIER.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU GET THE
ACADEMY AWARD OR THE EMMY?
>> I GET THE ACADEMY, HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS NICE.
>> WOW.
THAT'S COOL.
YOU WON'T SEE ANY FLIP-FLOPPING
HERE.
WHEN I SHAKE-- WHEN I DO THAT
RIGHT THERE, MY WORD IS MY BOND.
>> TONIGHT I'M SITTING IN A GOOD
SPOT IN THIS TRIBE, BUT TOMORROW
MORNING WHEN I GET UP, I NEED TO
GET ANDREA FEELING OKAY ABOUT
EVERYTHING BECAUSE SHE'S SMART
ENOUGH TO
KNOW THAT WE DOUBLE CROSSED HER,
AND SHE WILL DEFINITELY HOLD
THAT RESENTMENT.
>> OPEN IT UP.
>> OKAY.
"FOLLOW THE PATH TO THE ARENA
WHERE YOU WILL COMPETE IN A
DUEL.
THE WINNER OF THE DUEL WILL
CONTINUE TO LIVE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND AND AWAIT YOUR NEXT
OPPONENT.
THE LOSER GOES HOME THIS TIME
FOR GOOD."
>> THIS TIME FOR GOOD.
APPARENTLY WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
AN ARENA DUEL SOMEWHERE.
>> TREE MAIL.
THIS ONE'S GOING TO BE AN
INTERESTING ONE.
>> "TODAY YOU WON'T BE
COMPETING.
CHOOSE TWO WHO WILL GET A CHANCE
TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU LET
YOUR GUARD DOWN AT A PLACE WHICH
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE, REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
EACH OF YOU WILL REACH INTO THE
BAG AND TAKE ONE STONE."
>> OKAY, WHITE.
>> "IF YOU CHOOSE YOUR TRIBE-
COLORED STONE YOU WILL GO ON
THIS ADVENTURE."
>> WHITE.
SO THEN IT LOOKS LIKE ME AND
STEVE ARE GOING.
TREE MAIL TODAY
BASICALLY SAID TWO PEOPLE FROM
THE TRIBE ARE GOING TO GO TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
STEVE AND I WERE THE ONES WHO
ENDED UP TO BE THE ONES TO GO TO
THE DUEL.
>> GOOD-BYE, GUYS.
>> REMEMBER EVERYTHING YOU SEE.
>> AT REDEMPTION ISLAND I'M NOT
EXACTLY SURE WHAT TO EXPECT, BUT
I'M GLAD THAT RUSSELL AND
STEPHANIE AND CHRIS DIDN'T
HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO GO SO
THEY DON'T HAVE AN IDEA OF
WHAT'S THERE.
>> ON THREE.
>> TURN THEM OVER, ALL RIGHT.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> HEY, GUYS!
>> HEY!
>> WE PICKED MARBLES AND ASHLEY
AND I GET TO GO AND WATCH THE
DUEL BETWEEN FRAN AND MATT SO
I'M PRETTY EXCITED.
IT'S PROBABLY MORE ABOUT SEEING
MATT BECAUSE WE'RE REALLY CLOSE
AND I THINK IF HE REALIZES I
WASN'T THE ONE THAT VOTED HIM
OUT HE COULD COME BACK AND BE AN
ASSET FOR ME TO HAVE.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> HAVE FUN.
>> WE HAD TO SEND TWO PEOPLE TO
WHAT WE THINK IS REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
WE'VE GOT ANDREA AND ASHLEY BOTH
GOING OVER THERE.
WHAT I DON'T WANT IS ANDREA
GETTING SMART AND TALKING TO
MATT, HER ISLAND BOYFRIEND.
I JUST DON'T WANT HER GETTING
ANY IDEAS.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
FRANCESCA AND MATT, VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
THIS IS WHERE ALL THE DUELS WILL
TAKE PLACE.
EACH TRIBE SELECTED TWO TRIBE
MEMBERS TO BE A WITNESS TO YOUR
DUEL TODAY.
STEVE AND DAVE, AND ASHLEY AND
ANDREA.
MATT, FRANCESCA, BOTH OF YOU
VOTED OUT BY YOUR TRIBE MEMBERS
FOR WHATEVER REASON.
THEY DIDN'T WANT YOU AROUND
ANYMORE.
THIS IS THE FIRST STEP IN YOUR
JOURNEY TO GET EVEN.
>> I DIDN'T VOTE FOR EITHER OF
THEM.
>> Jeff: MATT, WHAT'S GOING
THROUGH YOUR HEAD RIGHT NOW?
>> IT'S DO-OR-DIE TIME SO, LIKE,
I'M READY TO GO.
IT'S GOING TO BE THE GREATEST
UNDERDOG STORY IF I GET
BLINDSIDED BY MY TRIBE WITH NONE
OF MY STUFF EXCEPT FOR WHAT I
HAVE ON AND COME BACK ALL THE
WAY AND MAKE IT TO THE END.
>> Jeff: FRANCESCA, EVEN THOUGH
YOU GUYS WERE TRIBEMATES AT THE
BEGINNING, ARE YOU ADVERSARIES
NOW?
>> I WISH MATT VERY WELL IN HIS
LIFE, BUT I DEFINITELY AM HERE
TO BEAT HIM IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET TO
TODAY'S DUEL.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU ARE GOING
TO USE STICKS AND ROPE TO MAKE A
LONG POLE.
YOU'LL USE THAT POLE TO RETRIEVE
THREE KEYS.
THOSE THREE KEYS OPEN THREE
LOCKS.
FIRST PERSON THROUGH THEIR DOOR
STAYS ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
LOSER IS OUT.
THEIR SHOT AT THE MILLION
DOLLARS, DONE.
IT'S ONE SHOT.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
THIS IS IT. DO-OR-DIE TIME.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
IT'S A GOOD OLD-FASHIONED
"SURVIVOR" CHALLENGE-- STICKS
AND ROPES AND LOCKS.
WINNER OF THIS CHALLENGE STAYS
ALIVE, CONTINUES THEIR QUEST FOR
A MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
LOSERS WILL LEAVE THE ARENA FOR
GOOD, OUT OF THE GAME.
FRANCESCA GOING TO GIVE IT A GO
WITH HER STICK.
SHE PUT THAT TOGETHER QUICKLY.
WILL IT BE STRONG ENOUGH TO
RETRIEVE THAT FIRST KEY?
IT LOOKS LIKE IT.
STEADY.
NICE JOB.
FRANCESCA RETRIEVES THAT FIRST
KEY.
MATT GIVES IT A SHOT, AND HIS
STICK FALLS APART RIGHT AWAY.
FRANCESCA GIVING HER STICK A
LITTLE ONCE-OVER.
SHE'S GOING TO GO BACK NOW AND
TRY FOR A SECOND KEY.
SHE'S VERY CLOSE.
CAN SHE GET IT OFF THE PEG?
YES.
NOW CAN SHE GET IT BACK?
DOING A GREAT JOB.
FRANCESCA HAS HER SECOND KEY,
ONE KEY LEFT.
>> GET IT, GET IT.
>> Jeff: MATT IS GOING TO HAVE
TO PICK IT UP NOW, START TAKING
SOME CHANCES.
HE'S ON IT.
OH, THAT STICK IS NOT GOING TO
STAY TOGETHER.
FRANCESCA GOING FOR THAT THIRD
KEY.
THIS COULD BE IT FOR FRANCESCA.
THAT KEY IS A LITTLE FURTHER
OUT, THOUGH.
CAN SHE REACH IT?
SHE'S THERE.
OH! STICK BREAKS.
MATT GIVING IT ANOTHER GO.
MATT HAS THE KEY HOOKED.
HE HAS IT OFF THE PEG.
MATT HAS HIS FIRST KEY BACK.
MATT NOW GOING FOR THE SECOND
KEY.
THAT STICK LOOKS LIKE IT'S
WORKING NOW.
GOTTA GET IT OFF THAT PEG.
MATT GOING FOR THAT SECOND KEY,
AND HE HAS IT.
CAN HE GET IT THROUGH THE GATE?
YES.
MATT HAS HIS SECOND KEY.
FRANCESCA GOING FOR THAT
THIRD KEY.
MATT NOW GOING FOR HIS THIRD
KEY.
BOTH MATT AND FRANCESCA HAVE ONE
KEY LEFT.
YOU WANT TO STAY ALIVE, YOU NEED
TO GET IT GOING RIGHT NOW.
IS THE POLE LONG ENOUGH?
HE'S ON THE KEY, JUST SHORT,
USING
EVERY PART OF HIS BODY, STILL
SHORT, AN INCH, HALF AN INCH
SHORT, MAYBE.
FRANCESCA HAS THE KEY.
MATT JUST MISSES GRABBING THE
KEY.
FRANCESCA-- OH!
JUST MISSED HOOKING IT.
MATT IS LONG ENOUGH.
IS IT STRONG ENOUGH?
MATT HAS THE THIRD KEY.
HE'S GOT TO GET IT THROUGH THE
GATE.
HE'S HOLDING ON.
MATT HAS ALL THREE KEYS!
HE CAN START OPENING THE LOCKS.
FRANCESCA NEEDS TO MAKE A MOVE
QUICKLY.
MATT HAS THE FIRST LOCK OPEN.
MATT HAS THE SECOND LOCK OPEN.
THIS IS IT FOR FRANCESCA.
MATT HAS THE THIRD LOCK OPEN.
MATT STAYS ALIVE!
>> GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
GIVE 'EM HELL.
>> Jeff: MATT, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU SEIZED THE MOMENT.
YOU ARE STILL ALIVE IN THIS
GAME.
FRANCESCA, YOUR SHOT AT
REDEMPTION AND THE MILLION-
DOLLAR PRIZE IS OVER.
YOU'RE OUT OF THE GAME.
YOU CAN TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE
FIRE ON YOUR WAY OUT.
>> BYE, HONEY.
>> LOVE YOU, FRANNY.
>> Jeff: MATT, YOU CAN HEAD BACK
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND, AWAIT YOUR
NEXT OPPONENT.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
>> BECAUSE IT'S NOT EVEN CLOSE
TO THE CAMP WE HAD BACK AT
OMETEPE, AND BEING BY YOURSELF
IT'S DEFINITELY HARD, BUT I
MEAN, GOTTA SEIZE THE MOMENT.
>> Jeff: IT'S ON YOU.
GET BACK TO REDEMPTION. MAKE IT
HAPPEN.
>> WILL DO.
>> Jeff: GUYS, YOU CAN HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
AS ALWAYS, WHATEVER YOU
WITNESSED
HERE, WHEN YOU GO BACK TO CAMP,
UP TO YOU WHAT YOU SHARE.
HEAD ON OUT.
>> GOING TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
WAS AN EYE OPENER.
THERE MIGHT BE AN OPPORTUNITY
HERE.
I'M THINKING THERE MIGHT BE SOME
CURVEBALL FOR RUSSELL TO TELL
THEM THAT FRANCESCA WON THE
CHALLENGE AND SENT MATT HOME.
>> THEY'RE BACK!
>> OH!
>> OH, THEY MADE IT.
>> YEAH, ALL RIGHT!
>> IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK!
>> WELCOME BACK.
>> HOW'S MATT?
>> HE'S GOOD.
>> HE'S PISSED. YOU CAN TELL.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> WE DIDN'T GET TO TALK TO HIM.
HE KEPT LOOKING UP AT US AND
SAYING HE WANTS TO COME BACK AND
GET HIS REVENGE.
>> REDEMPTION ISLAND IS REAL.
I MEAN, THERE'S A CHANCE MATT
COULD RUN THE GAMUT OVER THERE
AND COME BACK INTO THIS GAME.
ANDREA WILL GO BACK TO MATT
BEFORE SHE'LL STAY WITH ME.
I KNOW THAT.
SO I'VE GOT MY WORK CUT OUT FOR
ME WITH ANDREA.
I LIKE YOU, ANDREA, AND I THINK
YOU'RE A GOOD-HEARTED KID, YOU
KNOW.
I'M SORRY WHAT HAPPENED, YOU
I AM.
AND, LIKE, IF I COULD HAVE
THOUGHT OF ANY OTHER WAY, THEN I
WOULD HAVE.
BUT IT WASN'T JUST ME.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> THERE WERE FOUR PEOPLE THAT
WERE INVOLVED IN IT.
FOUR PEOPLE AGREED TO IT.
FOUR PEOPLE TALKED ABOUT IT.
NOBODY WANTED TO DO IT.
>> NO, BUT I DON'T KNOW WHERE I
STAND NOW.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, YOU'RE STILL
IN THE-- LIKE, I KNOW, IT'S
CRAZY.
>> SO PHILLIP AND CHRISTINE ARE
GOING BEFORE ME?
>> YEAH.
>> I TALKED TO ROB, AND HE
ASSURED ME THAT I'M STILL PART
OF THEIR FIVE, EVEN THOUGH I
HAVE A FEELING I'M PROBABLY IN A
REALLY STICKY POSITION.
SO RIGHT NOW, STRATEGICALLY
IT'S SMART TO STAY WITH THEM AND
MAKE SURE THEY DON'T THINK I'M
SCHEMING, BUT I JUST DON'T
BELIEVE HIM.
I NEED IN SOME WAY TO MIX THINGS
UP BECAUSE, LIKE, DEEP DOWN,
I'M LIKE STILL REALLY PISSED
ABOUT WHAT THEY DID.
THEY, LIKE, TOOK MY GOOD FRIEND
AWAY.
>> THE TWO BLONDES.
THEY WERE SITTING UP WITH US IN
A GLADIATOR STADIUM.
>> WHO WON?
>> THE BLACK CHICK PULLED IT OFF
AND THE BLOND KID HE WENT HOME.
WE CAME BACK FROM REDEMPTION
ISLAND AND WE TOLD RUSSELL THAT
MATT WAS SENT HOME.
>> FIRST OUT, SURFER GUY.
>> SO WHENEVER WE VOTE RUSSELL
OUT, HE'LL GET OVER THERE AND
SEE MATT, WHO COULD BE A-- QUITE
A CHALLENGE FOR HIM AND
HOPEFULLY WE'LL NEVER SEE
RUSSELL AGAIN.
>> ACTUALLY, THE BLACK GIRL WENT
HOME.
>> THE BLACK GIRL WENT HOME?
>> THE BLOND DUDE IS THERE.
I JUST WANTED HIM TO BE SHOCKED.
I JUST WANT HIM TO BE SHOCKED
WHEN HE GETS THERE AND HE'S
WRESTLING THE BLOND DUDE.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> I KNOW IT IS 6-3.
SO RIGHT NOW, THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING FOR ME IS FINDING THE
IDOL.
IF I FIND THE IDOL, RUSSELL GETS
ANOTHER BLINDSIDE.
"WHERE SOMETHING IS ALIVE
NEXT TO SOMETHING THAT'S NOT."
THAT'S WHAT IT'S TALKING ABOUT.
AT THE LAST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE I
GOT THE CLUE FOR THE IDOL, BUT
IT'S SO VAGUE.
"SOMETHING THAT'S ALIVE," THE
BEACH IS DEFINITELY ALIVE.
EVERYTHING OUT HERE IS ALIVE,
THE TREES, THE RUNNING WATER.
WHERE IS THE IDOL?
THE CLUE SAID IT WAS BY
SOMETHING ALIVE NEXT TO
SOMETHING NOT.
MY MIND IS RUNNING 100 MILES PER
HOUR.
>> RUSSELL AND THEM ARE STILL
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL JUST AS
HARD AS THEY CAN LOOK BUT HE
AIN'T GOING TO GET IT NOW.
'CAUSE I'VE GOT IT.
AND I'M NOT SAYING NOTHING ABOUT
IT, SO THIS IS NOT RUSSELL'S
GAME NO MORE.
IT'S MY GAME.
>> I JUST DON'T THINK IT'S HERE.
>> THE GREAT THING WITH RUSSELL
IS THAT HE HAS A GREAT RESUME
WITH IMMUNITY IDOLS THAT HE'S
FOUND ON HIS OWN.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO PUT IT
ALL IN YOUR PURSE.
>> YEAH.
SO WE ARE GOING TO FAKE THAT
WE HAVE THE IDOL.
AND I AM HOPING THAT PEOPLE
BELIEVE I'M PROTECTING THE
IMMUNITY IDOL.
BUT RIGHT NOW, IT IS JUST A
BLANK
CHECK WITH NO MONEY IN THE BANK
ACCOUNT.
( LAUGHS )
>> SHE'S KEEPING A TIGHT HOLD OF
THAT BAG, ISN'T SHE?
>> YOU KNOW IT.
>> ALL BUTTONED UP.
DON'T BURN THAT BAG, DARLING.
THERE'S GOLD IN THERE.
YOU WANT ME TO HOLD IT FOR YOU
FOR A WHILE?
I DIDN'T KNOW IF YOUR LEGS WERE
GETTING TIRED.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I LIKE TO WATCH THE TWO GIRLS
WITH THAT BAG.
I WANT TO.
I MEAN, WATCH THEM. WATCH THEM.
>> WE KNEW THAT RUSSELL AND HIS
LITTLE HAREM HAVE GOT THE FIRST
IMMUNITY CLUE.
STEPHANIE'S CARRYING THE BAG
AROUND ACTING LIKE SHE HAS THE
IDOL IN THERE.
>> WHEN RUSSELL ORDERS IT, THEY
DO IT.
>> I KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU DO IT,
BROTHER.
RUSSELL IS ALWAYS PLOTTING AND
SCHEMING.
YOU JUST DON'T WANT THE GUY
AROUND.
YOU KNOW HE'S GOING TO DO
EVERYTHING HE CAN TO BACKSTAB
YOU.
WE JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE WE
STAY ON OUR TOES UNTIL THAT
CANCER IS CUT OUT.
>> YOU SHOULD JUST LAY DOWN LIKE
THAT.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS DOING.
>> THIS ONE DOESN'T LOOK BAD.
IT'S CLEARING UP.
>> YEAH, THAT ONE IS CLEARING
UP.
>> RUSSELL HAS GOT SOME FUNK
GOING ON WITH HIS ARMPITTS.
HE SHAVED THEM UP AND NOW HE'S
GOT
A PUSS-FILLED RASH ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
I MEAN, IT'S DISGUSTING.
>> IT FEELS LIKE IT'S GETTING
WORSE.
>> HE SITS IN THE TENT WITH HIS
CONCUBINES AND DOES NOTHING.
HE'S LIKE A BLACK HOLE, YOU
KNOW, SUCKING IN ENERGY AND
LIGHT, EVERYTHING.
>> I REALLY THINK-- MY FEELING
IS GET RID OF RUSSELL SOONER
THAN LATER.
>> OH, YEAH. THE SOONER THE
BETTER.
>> HE'D BE NO GOOD-- HE'D BE NO
GOOD-- HE'D BE A THORN IN OUR
SIDE TO KEEP AROUND UNTIL THE
MERGE.
>> I AGREE.
>> HE AIN'T DOING A THING.
>> HE'S NOT LIFTING ANY LOGS.
>> HE AIN'T CARRYING NO WOOD,
NOT CATCHING ANYTHING TO EAT.
>> YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY ALWAYS
THINKS
YOU DON'T WANT TO THROW A
CHALLENGE.
THERE HASN'T BEEN A LOT OF
SUCCESS THROWING CHALLENGES
BECAUSE ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU'RE
DOWN NUMBERS BUT HE'S NOT A
NUMBER.
>> NO.
>> THERE REALLY IS NOTHING
BIGGER AT THIS POINT THAN TO GET
RID OF RUSSELL.
HE'S AN IRRITANT.
YOU CANNOT HAVE THIS GUY LAY
AROUND AND POTENTIALLY BITE ANY
ONE OF US.
>> HEY, SO LET ME THROW THIS OUT
HERE TO YOU.
IF WE HAD A CHALLENGE OR
SOMETHING WOULD IT MAKE SENSE TO
THROW IT AND JUST GET RID OF
RUSSELL BEFORE HE EVEN FINDS THE
SECOND CLUE OR THIRD CLUE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO THROW THINGS,
BUT HE'S LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
HE'S BROKEN RIGHT NOW.
HE'S GOT RASHES EVERYWHERE.
HE HURTS LIKE HELL.
THIS IS THE TIME WHEN YOU LAY
THE FINAL BLOW.
>> ONLY THING WITH THROWING ONE,
YOU GUYS, IS THAT THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO BE GETTING RID OF ONE
MORE PERSON AND THEY MIGHT START
GETTING A ROLL GOING AND IT
COULD REVERSE ON US.
THEY'RE THINKING ABOUT THROWING
OUR NEXT CHALLENGE.
I'M JUST TORN.
I'M TORN ABOUT THAT.
BECAUSE I LIKE TO COMPETE, AND I
CAN DEAL WITH RUSSELL.
>> WE'LL DECIDE WHEN WE GET
THERE.
ONE THUMBS UP MEANS WE'RE
THROWING IT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> WE ARE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ZAPATERA,
ONCE AGAIN I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, THREE
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL BE
STRAPPED TO A LARGE WHEEL.
THREE OTHER MEMBERS WILL WORK
TOGETHER TO SPIN THE WHEEL.
AS THE WHEEL TURNS, YOU WILL GO
UNDERWATER, GRAB A MOUTHFUL OF
WATER, COME BACK TO THE TOP, AND
SPIT THE WATER OUT INTO A TUBE.
ONCE THE TUBE FILLS, A BALL
WILL ROLL DOWN TO A SLIDE PUZZLE
WHERE ONE TRIBE MEMBER MUST
SOLVE THE PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET THEIR BALL
THROUGH THE COMPLETED SLIDE
PUZZLE WINS IMMUNITY AND IS SAFE
FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: A LOT OF COMFORT ITEMS
HERE.
YOU HAVE A COUPLE OF CHAIRS.
PILLOWS, TARP, THREE BLANKETS,
AND A LANTERN.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE THE THIRD PERSON WILL BE
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME AND SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
ZAPATERA, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
TRIBE MEMBERS-- SITTING TWO
PEOPLE OUT.
>> THERE'S DEFINITELY A BIG
TRADEOFF THERE BETWEEN KEEPING
RUSSELL AROUND AND GETTING A
TARP BUT THE PLAN AS IT STANDS
RIGHT NOW IS TO THROW THE
CHALLENGE.
HOPEFULLY THE END RESULT IS
WORTH IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WHO'S IT
GOING TO BE, ZAPATERA?
>> RALPH AND SERITA.
>> Jeff: SERITA AND RALPH, TAKE
A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
>> I'M GOING TO DO THE PUZZLE
PART.
YOU GUYS WORK THE WHEEL.
>> JULIE.
>> SHE'S GONNA JUST BE MISSING
THE BUCKET.
MISS THE BUCKET. MISS THE
BUCKET.
IF YOU WANT TO THROW IT.
>> RIGHT NOW THE PLAN IS TO
THROW THE CHALLENGE.
IT'S A DECISION I'M NOT REALLY
FEELING RIGHT WITH.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
NATALIE WITH A LOT OF WATER.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: STEPHANIE WITH A GOOD
SPIT OF WATER.
BOTH TRIBES DOING VERY WELL.
TAKES A LOT OF GUTS TO BE THE
PEOPLE ON THE WHEEL BEING THROWN
UNDERWATER EVERY FEW SECONDS TO
TAKE IN A MOUTHFUL OF WATER AND
THEN SPIT IT INTO A TUBE.
>> COME ON.
>> Jeff: KRISTINA WITH A GOOD
JOB.
KRISTA DOES A NICE JOB.
JULIE MISSES.
OMETEPE HAS THIS NAILED.
ZAPATERA NOT SO MUCH.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: STEVE SEEMS TO BE
WEARING OUT.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE RELEASES THEIR
BALL.
ROB CAN NOW START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
>> COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
>>Jeff: BIG HEAD START FOR ROB.
>> LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
>> LET'S GO, ROB!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA REALLY SLOWING
DOWN.
DAVID WOULD LIKE TO HAVE A SHOT
AT THIS PUZZLE.
>> GOOD JOB, ROB!
>> Jeff: ROB WORKING QUICKLY ON
THE SLIDE PUZZLE.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> COME ON, STEF!
THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA RELEASES THEIR
BALL.
DAVID CAN START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
>> COME ON, DAVE.
>> Jeff: IT IS A SHOWDOWN
BETWEEN THE PUZZLE MAKERS.
DAVID AND ROB.
ZAPATERA WON IN THIS SHOWDOWN AT
THE VERY FIRST CHALLENGE.
ROB LOOKING FOR A LITTLE
REDEMPTION, WOULD LIKE TO BRING
HOME IMMUNITY FOR OMETEPE.
ZAPATERA HAS YET TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> COME ON, DAVE, YOU CAN DO
THIS.
>> Jeff: ROB MAKING SOME
PROGRESS.
>> COME ON, DAVE.
>> Jeff: DAVE BARELY WORKING.
>> YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD, ROB,
KEEP IT UP.
>> Jeff: ROB GETTING CLOSER TO
THE FINISH.
>> COME ON ROB!
>> COME ON DAVID!
COME ON, YOU'RE THE MAN!
>> YEAH, ROB!
>> THERE YOU GO, ROB.
>> Jeff: ROB THINKS HE HAS IT.
>> GO, ROB!
>> Jeff: ROB HAS IT.
HE'S GOT THE BALL IN THE
CHANNEL.
IT'S AS EASY AS THAT.
OMETEPE WINS THEIR FIRST
CHALLENGE!
REWARD AND IMMUNITY.
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
ROB, FIRST WIN FOR THIS TRIBE.
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
>> OVERDUE.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR REWARD.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
ALL RIGHT, ZAPATERA, NEW
EXPERIENCE TONIGHT.
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE YOU WILL
VOTE YOUR FIRST PERSON OUT OF
THE TRIBE.
THAT PERSON WILL GO TO
REDEMPTION AND WILL HAVE TO
COMPETE IN A DUEL TO STAY ALIVE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF. HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL.
>> IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER,
I WOULD THINK THEY THREW THE
CHALLENGE.
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM LET THE
CHALLENGE GO.
I'M DEALING WITH A BUNCH OF
BITCHES.
>> WE WON TODAY'S IMMUNITY AND
REWARD CHALLENGE, AND NORMALLY,
THAT WOULD PUT ME THROUGH THE
ROOF HAPPY.
BUT NOW WE HAVE THESE LITTLE
THINGS CALLED HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOLS.
NOW I KNOW ENOUGH THAT THERE'S
PROBABLY A CLUE TO THAT HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL SOMEWHERE HIDDEN
WITHIN OUR REWARD, AND IT WAS
ALMOST AS IF THERE WAS NO TIME
TO CELEBRATE BECAUSE EVERYBODY'S
LOOKING FOR WHERE THE CLUE COULD
BE.
THE GAME IS ALWAYS ON.
IN THE PAST, I IGNORED THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
WELL, THAT DIDN'T TURN OUT TOO
GOOD FOR ME.
SO THIS TIME AROUND I DECIDED
MAYBE I CAN LEARN SOMETHING,
TOO.
SO I'M STARTING TO LOOK FOR
THEM, AND I'M STARTING TO BE
DILIGENT ABOUT IT.
I WENT THROUGH EVERYTHING.
AND IT WAS NOWHERE.
I LOOK OVER AND I SEE PHILLIP'S
FAT ASS BENDING THE CHAIR ABOUT
TO BREAK IT.
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
>> IT FEELS GOOD.
>> WHY IS IT LOPSIDED?
>> IT'S PROBABLY MISSING A SCREW
AND I'M PROBABLY NOT ON EVEN
GROUND.
>> HOLD ON.
YEAH, DON'T BECAUSE YOU'RE GONNA
BREAK IT.
>> THINK SO?
>> SIT OVER HERE.
GET A SCREW.
>> I LOOKED DOWN AND THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE IS RIGHT
UNDERNEATH HIS ASS.
IT'S SITTING, SEWN INSIDE THE
FABRIC OF THE CHAIR.
I GOTTA FIX THIS.
I THINK I HAVE A SCREW IN THE
TOOLBOX.
SWEET.
"ROCKS, TREES, LOGS, AND SAND.
FORAGING, CLIMBING OR MAYBE
DIGGING YOU'LL BE.
THE IDOL IS NEAR ONE OF THE
ABOVE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO EXPLORE THEM ALL
TO SEE."
THE CLUE BASICALLY COULD HAVE
READ "THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
IS SOMEWHERE."
I MEAN, IT COULD BE ANYWHERE.
I'M HAPPY THAT I FOUND THE CLUE
BECAUSE I KNOW NOW THAT NOBODY
ELSE FOUND THE CLUE.
I'M GOING DOWN FOR A LITTLE CRAB
ATTACK.
BUT I DON'T PLAN ON TELLING
ANYBODY ABOUT THE CLUE BECAUSE I
WANT THE IDOL FOR ME.
>> LET'S GET THE FIRE GOING.
>> I'LL GET IT. I'LL GET IT.
WELL, IT WAS A THROWN CHALLENGE.
BECAUSE WE DO GOTTA GET RUSSELL
OUT AS QUICK AS POSSIBLE.
RUSSELL THINKS HE RUNS THE SHOW,
AND HE DON'T.
HE'S NOT MY BOSS AND HE'S NOT
BOSS OF ME.
>> DO WE HAVE A PLAN?
>> YEAH.
>> STICKING TO THAT?
>> STICKING TO THE PLAN.
WE'RE GOING TO GO 3-3.
>> THE PLAN TONIGHT IS TO GIVE
THREE VOTES TO RUSSELL AND THREE
VOTES TO STEPHANIE IN THE
ABSOLUTELY REMOTE, RARE EVENT
THAT RUSSELL DID FIND AN IDOL.
SO IF EVERYTHING GOES AS PLANNED
TONIGHT, RUSSELL WILL GO HOME.
>> IT'S STUPID TO THROW
CHALLENGES WHEN YOU ARE ONLY TWO
UP.
I CAN SEE IF YOU'RE FIVE UP OR
SOMETHING, FOUR UP, MAYBE.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT TWO UP?
WHEN THE GAME JUST STARTED?
WHAT DO THEY WANT TO GO EVEN AT
THE MERGE?
I THINK THEY THREW THE
CHALLENGE.
IT MAKES ME SICK TO MY STOMACH
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO WIN RIGHT
NOW.
YOU CAN'T GIVE BOSTON ROB
MOMENTUM.
NOT IN THIS GAME.
IF THEY SPLIT THE VOTES, IT WILL
BE A TWO-WAY TIE.
ONE WILL BE SAFE, THEY WOULD
REVOTE AND I WOULD GO HOME.
I HAVE TO CONVINCE SOMEBODY TO
FLIP.
ONE PERSON.
>> TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, WE
WERE THINKING THE VOTES WOULD BE
SPLIT 3-3-3 BECAUSE THEY WOULD
WANT TO FLUSH OUT THE IDOL AND
GET RID OF ONE OF US.
SO ALL IT WOULD TAKE IS FOR ONE
OF THEIR SIX TO FLIP ON THEM AND
VOTE WITH US, SO THAT WE WOULD
GET THE MAJORITY OF THE VOTES.
>> DO YOU THINK... THE OLD LADY
WILL?
>> OKAY.
>> WOULD IT BE WEIRD IF I ASKED
YOU WHERE DO YOU THINK EXACTLY
YOU STAND WITH THE SIX PEOPLE
YOU HAVE?
WE KNOW THAT WE HAVE OUR ONE,
TWO, THREE.
>> RIGHT. YOU GUYS ARE STRONG.
>> YOU KNOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WELL, WE HAVE STUFF UP OUR
SLEEVES.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
WE'RE LOOKING FOR THE FOURTH
PERSON.
>> SEE, AND RUSSELL KNOWS HOW TO
GET TO THE END.
>> AND WE HAVE THE IDOL.
>> RIGHT ON.
>> WE SHOULD SIT DOWN. I'M
GETTING...
>> YOU'RE GETTING LIGHTHEADED.
AND TO BE HONEST I LIKE MY
CHANCES WITH SOMEBODY WHO HAS
BEEN THERE BEFORE A COUPLE TIMES
BEFORE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> IF I DO BECOME A FOURTH...
>> YOU NEED TO REMEMBER, HE WILL
TAKE US TO THE TOP.
AND THEN AFTER THAT...
>> IT MAKES SENSE. I MEAN, IT
MAKES SENSE.
>> IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
>> THIS IS A GAME TURNER RIGHT
HERE, THIS VOTE.
SO, IT'S A LOT OF PRESSURE.
I HAVE THOUGHT IT OUT BOTH WAYS.
SHOULD I GO WITH RUSSELL?
SHOULD I TRUST HIM?
BECAUSE I KNOW HOW GOOD HE IS.
>> SHE'S ON OUR SIDE.
>> OKAY. NOW, I'M GOING TO TALK
TO HER.
>> OKAY. THIS IS GOING TO BE THE
BIGGEST BLINDSIDE EVER.
>> IF YOU-- IF YOU DO THIS, IF
THIS GOES THE WAY IT GOES, I GOT
YOUR ( NO AUDIO ) BACK.
>> OKAY, I TRUST YOU, DUDE.
>> LET'S DO IT.
RALPH.
LET'S GET RID OF RALPH.
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU DO THIS
WITH ME, I GOT YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IF THIS HAPPENS, GAME ON.
THIS WILL BE THE BIGGEST MOVE,
BIGGER THAN ANY MOVE I'VE EVER
MADE.
THIS WILL BE A SHOCKER.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT RIGHT
THERE.
"KEEP HOPE ALIVE" BABY.
THIS AIN'T OVER TILL IT'S OVER.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS A
TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH AND
APPROACH THE FLAME.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
WITH A SLIGHT EXCEPTION THIS
SEASON: REDEMPTION ISLAND.
SO, RALPH, FIRST TIME TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> WELL, IT'S GOOD AND IT'S BAD.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT
COMING TO TRIBAL?
>> WELL, I WAS TOLD WE HAD TWO
PARTS IN OUR GAME.
>> Jeff: I'M LOST. TWO PARTS?
>> WE'VE GOT TWO TEAMS IN THE
SAME TEAM.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE SAYING THERE'S A
DIVISION WITHIN THE TRIBE.
>> YES, A DIVISION.
>> Jeff: STEVE, WAS IT QUICKLY
APPARENT WHO WAS JELLING WITH
WHO?
>> YES, IT WAS, JEFF.
THERE ARE SIX OF US THAT ARE
PRETTY ROCK SOLID, AND THEN
THERE'S ANOTHER THREE LED BY
RUSSELL.
>> Jeff: SERITA, WHAT CAUSED THE
DIVISION WITHIN THIS TRIBE?
>> I THINK IT WAS A LOT TO DO
WITH RUSSELL AND HIS LEGACY, AND
RUSSELL HAD GIVEN THIS GREAT
SPEECH ABOUT HOW HE WAS GOING TO
PLAY DIFFERENTLY AND THAT TURNED
OUT NOT TO BE THE CASE SO THERE
WAS A HUGE FISSURE IN THE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL YOU HAD TO KNOW
YOU WERE COMING IN HERE WITH A
TARGET?
>> JEFF, THE PROBLEM WITH ME
COMING HERE EVERYBODY PERCEIVES
ME AS THAT LEGACY WHERE I WOULD
TRY TO LOSE BY BURNING SOCKS,
POURING OUT WATER.
I AM NOT PLAYING THAT GAME.
I CAME IN TO WIN CHALLENGES, NOT
TO LOSE CHALLENGES.
AND, YOU KNOW, FROM WHERE I
STOOD, IT FELT TO ME THAT A LOT
OF PEOPLE GAVE UP IN THE
CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: TODAY?
>> IT FELT THAT THEY THREW THE
CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: MIKE, BIG ACCUSATION.
>> PRETTY BIG.
YOU KNOW, TODAY I WOULD SAY WE
DIDN'T GO 100%.
WE DEFINITELY WANTED TO WIN, BUT
IF WE LOST, WE GOT SOME FAT ON
THIS TRIBE WE NEED TO TRIM OFF.
>> Jeff: JULIE, HARD TO CONSIDER
GETTING RID OF SOMEBODY WHEN YOU
KNOW THAT IT IS ABOUT NUMBERS,
QUITE OFTEN?
>> PERSONALLY, I WOULD LIKE TO
MERGE WITH AS MANY PEOPLE AS
POSSIBLE.
WEAK OR STRONG, WHETHER WE GET
ALONG OR NOT, I THINK WE NEED TO
GO INTO THE MERGE WITH NUMBERS.
>> Jeff: STEPHANIE, WHAT DO YOU
BELIEVE?
>> WELL, I THINK THE MAJORITY OF
THE TRIBE FORGET THAT THEY'RE IN
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
THIS IS RUSSELL.
HE'S PLAYED THE GAME.
HE WOULD BE A HUGE PART OF
MOVING FORWARD.
HE'S DONE IT TWICE.
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER, THERE'S
GOING TO BE BACKSTABBING MADE,
SO IF YOU GUYS WANT TO BECOME
BEST FRIENDS RIGHT NOW, THAT'S
FINE.
BUT YOUR BEST FRIEND TO THE LEFT
OF YOU, TO THE RIGHT OF YOU, IS
GOING TO TURN AROUND AND STAB
YOU IN THE BACK BECAUSE YOU
DON'T HAVE ENOUGH NUMBERS.
>> WHAT SHE DOESN'T REALIZE
IS...
>> I'M STILL TALKING, MOUTH IS
STILL MOVING, THANK YOU.
>> FEISTY!
>> HAVING THE NUMBERS IN THE
MERGE IS WHAT YOU NEED TO TAKE
OVER THE OTHER TRIBE.
WE WERE TWO PEOPLE ABOVE THEM,
GUYS.
SO THROWING TODAY'S CHALLENGE IS
NOT STRATEGY.
IT'S PLAIN STUPIDITY.
THAT'S ALL.
>> Jeff: STEVE, GOING INTO A
MERGE, AN INCOHESIVE GROUP OF
NINE IS A MUCH BIGGER ADVANTAGE
THAN A TIGHT SIX DOWN AT THE
MERGE.
THAT'S THE POINT STEPHANIE'S
MAKING.
>> IT STUNK NOT WINNING TODAY.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE SAYING
ABSOLUTELY NOT, YOU GUYS DID NOT
THROW THE CHALLENGE.
>> WE DID NOT THROW THE
CHALLENGE.
I WORKED MY TAIL OFF, AND I
THINK EVERYBODY ELSE DID, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO, DAVID, YOU GOT YOUR
ASS KICKED BY ROB HANDILY TODAY.
IT WASN'T EVEN CLOSE.
>> ROB BEAT ME.
>> REALLY?
FOR ME IT'S WEIRD BECAUSE
SOMEONE WHO DOES PUZZLES...
>> SOMEBODY SHOULDN'T SPEAK FOR
ME ON THAT NOTE, ACTUALLY.
I TAKE A LITTLE EXCEPTION TO ALL
THIS.
JUST BECAUSE THE HANDS AREN'T
MOVING DOESN'T MEAN THE MIND
ISN'T WORKING.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: SERITA, IS PART OF WHAT
IS SCARY ABOUT RUSSELL IS YOU
JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S GOING
TO SAY OR DO?
>> IT'S JUST A SICKNESS, ALMOST.
IT'S A HUGE BLACK CLOUD OVER
EVERYTHING WE DO.
HE DOES NOTHING AT CAMP...
>> WHAT'S THAT, STEPHANIE?
>> I REALLY CAN'T HEAR HER TO
SAY RUSSELL DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
HE GETS FIREWOOD.
WE CATCH CRAB.
DON'T SAY HE DOESN'T DO
ANYTHING.
WAKE UP, OKAY?
>> Jeff: RALPH, YOU HAD A HUGE
REACTION.
>> HE WON'T CATCH THE FISH BUT
HE WILL EAT EVERY PIECE THAT IS
BROUGHT IN.
>> Jeff: I THINK YOU SAID SHE'S
NOT HELPING AT ALL
TO DO ANYTHING, CATCH FISH, BUT
EAT IT.
>> NO.
>> Jeff: WE'RE EARLY IN THE GAME
AND YOU GUYS ARE SO DIVIDED
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE COME A MERGE.
BIG PREDICTION FROM ME, BUT I
THINK I'M RIGHT.
SO, RUSSELL, WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> YOU KNOW, I NEVER STOP
PLAYING THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE A NEW TATTOO
ON YOUR ARM, "KEEP HOPE ALIVE."
>> THAT'S ALL I HAVE RIGHT NOW
IS HOPE.
FIRST TIME I PLAYED I WAS
IN TROUBLE.
SECOND TIME I PLAYED, I WAS IN
TROUBLE.
I KNOW WHAT THEY THINK, BUT IT
NEVER IS WHAT IT SEEMS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
STEVE, YOU'RE UP.
>> I'M VOTING FOR YOU.
YOU ARE SO MISGUIDED AND SO
RUDE.
>> THIS IS MY GAME, SUCKER.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, RUSSELL.
RALPH.
STEPHANIE.
RUSSELL.
THAT'S TWO VOTES RUSSELL.
THAT'S THREE VOTES RUSSELL, ONE
VOTE RALPH, ONE VOTE STEPHANIE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES STEPHANIE,
THREE VOTES RUSSELL, ONE VOTE
RALPH.
TWO VOTES RALPH, TWO VOTES
STEPHANIE, THREE VOTES RUSSELL.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES RALPH, THREE VOTES
RUSSELL, TWO VOTES STEPHANIE,
ONE VOTE LEFT.
STEPHANIE.
WE HAVE A THREE-WAY TIE.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
STEPHANIE, RUSSELL, RALPH, YOU
WILL NOT VOTE.
EVERYBODY ELSE WILL VOTE, AND
YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR RALPH,
RUSSELL, OR STEPHANIE.
STEVE, IF YOU'LL GRAB THIS.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, RALPH.
RUSSELL.
THREE VOTES RUSSELL, ONE VOTE
RALPH.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,"
RUSSELL.
THAT'S FOUR. THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> I'LL BE BACK AND BE READY.
>> I'LL BE READY.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU JUST VOTED
OUT ONE OF THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
PLAYERS IN THE HISTORY OF
"SURVIVOR."
THE QUESTION IS: WILL THIS
DECISION COME BACK TO HAUNT YOU?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
PHIL'S ON THE HOT SEAT.
>> HE IS SO ANNOYING.
>> Jeff: BUT WITH THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL IN PLAY, ANYTHING
CAN HAPPEN.
>> SOMEBODY WITHIN MY ALLIANCE
MIGHT FLIP.
>> Jeff: AND AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND, IT'S TIME FOR RUSSELL TO
PUT UP OR SHUT UP.
>> THIS WAS THE REAL WORLD, I'D
BE ROOTING FOR MATT.
BUT IT'S NOT.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I'VE
EVER BEEN VOTED OUT.
I DON'T LIKE IT AT ALL.
I WAS PISSED OFF.
I WANTED TO BITCH-SLAP EVERY
SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
>> RUSSELL!
>> RIGHT NOW THIS IS HIS HOUSE.
I'M ABOUT TO TAKE IT FROM HIM.