>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION
ISLAND," RUSSELL.
FOR THE ZAPATERA TRIBE THE ONE
NIGHT OF PLEASURE THEY GOT FROM
THROWING A CHALLENGE TO GET RID
OF RUSSELL TURNED INTO DAYS OF
MISERY.
TRIBE UNITY CRUMBLED.
>> DAVID UNDER PRESSURE IS
REALLY STRESSFUL.
>> I DON'T FREAK OUT.
>> Jeff: AND DAVID'S
RELATIONSHIP WITH SARITA GOT SO
BAD HE JOINED FORCES WITH
STEPHANIE TO TRY TO VOTE SARITA
OUT.
>> STEPHANIE IS A CAPABLE
COMPETITOR IN THE CHALLENGES AND
I THINK UNQUESTIONABLY SARITA IS
THE WEAKEST PLAYER ON THE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: AT OMETEPE, ROB HAD A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IN HIS
POCKET ALONG WITH MOST OF HIS
TRIBE.
>> BY ME HAVING THIS I KNOW THAT
NOBODY ELSE HAS THIS.
>> Jeff: BUT PHILLIP HAD A
LOVE-HATE RELATIONSHIP WITH ROB.
>> I HAVE BEEN IN AN ALLIANCE
WITH ROB, GRANT, AND MYSELF.
>> Jeff: WHEN ROB TRIED TO
HIDE A CLUE TO
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
>> I SAW IT.
>> Jeff: IT WAS ALL-OUT WAR.
>> I'M GOING TO KICK A LITTLE
ASS AROUND HERE.
>> Jeff: NATALIE GOES SHORT!
OMETEPE WINS IMMUNITY!
THE OMETEPES WON THEIR THIRD OUT
OF THE LAST FOUR CHALLENGES.
THE ZAPATERAS WENT TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE DAVE AND STEPHANIE
VOTED FOR SARITA BUT EVERYONE
ELSE VOTED FOR STEPHANIE.
STEPHANIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
WITH STEPHANIE OFF TO A DUEL,
BOTH TRIBES ARE NOW EVEN AT SIX.
WELL, YOU MADE THE DECISION TO
GO WITH SOMEBODY YOU THINK YOU
CAN TRUST VERSUS KEEPING
SOMEBODY WHO MIGHT HAVE DONE
BETTER AT CHALLENGES.
WE'LL KNOW SOON ENOUGH IF YOU
MADE THE RIGHT CALL.
>> I HOPE WE CAN ALL COME
TOGETHER.
>> I KNOW DAVID AND SARITA HAVE
HAD SOME DIFFERENCES, BUT I HOPE
YOU GUYS CAN...
>> THE TWO VOTES AGAINST SARITA
WERE STEPHANIE AND MINE.
I DIDN'T WANT TO MAKE ANY BONES
ABOUT WHERE I STOOD.
I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO AND I
WANTED TO MAKE MY PLACE AND MY
POSITION KNOWN, AND IF IT'S THE
END OF ME, THEN SO BE IT.
>> I LOOK FORWARD TO MOVING
FORWARD, AND ALL PITCHING IN
LIKE WE'RE ALL DOING AROUND
CAMP.
>> ME, TOO, ME, TOO.
AND I DO LOVE CONSTRUCTIVE
FEEDBACK AND I DO NEED TO BUCK
UP MORE.
TRIBAL IS NEVER GOOD BUT TONIGHT
WAS ESPECIALLY BAD BECAUSE COME
TO FIND OUT OUR GANG OF SIX DID
HAVE A MAJOR HOLE IN IT, WHICH
AS I HAD SUSPECTED, DAVID HAD
GONE OVER TO THE DARK SIDE, TO
STEPHANIE.
>> WELL, LET'S DO THE BEST WE
CAN TO FUNCTION AS A TRIBE
BECAUSE IT'S IN ALL OUR
COLLECTIVE BEST INTERESTS.
>> I AGREE.
>> THIS IS THE SIX WE'VE WANTED
BACK IN DAY ONE, BUT THERE'S A
BIG RIFT BETWEEN DAVID AND
SARITA.
>> FIND COMMON GROUND LIKE
WE DID BACK IN DAY TWO AND
THREE.
>> I AGREE.
AND I HAVE A TON OF RESPECT FOR
YOU, DAVID.
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO GIVE ME A
SPEECH. IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> DAVE IS SHOWING HE CAN BE A
BIT OF AN ANTAGONIST BUT
HOPEFULLY DAVID CAN BE MAN
ENOUGH AND PUT HIS EGO AND PRIDE
AND EMOTIONS ASIDE AND, YOU
KNOW, FOR THE BIGGER CAUSE OF
THE TEAM.
IF NOT, THERE COULD BE PROBLEMS.
>> I MEAN, THERE ARE SO MANY
THINGS I LOVE, I LOVE VIETNAMESE
FOOD, THAI FOOD, I LIKE CHINESE
FOOD, I LOVE ITALIAN.
I DON'T EVEN LIKE SWEETS BUT
BRING IT ON AND I'M GOING TO
HAVE A SLICE OF RED VELVET FROM
A BAKERY I USED TO WORK AT.
THE WEIRDEST THING I'VE BEEN
CRAVING IS A BANANA SHAKE WITH
PEANUT BUTTER IN IT.
LIKE I WANT THE TASTE OF PEANUT
BUTTER LIKE SNICKER DOODLES WITH
PEANUT BUTTER ON TOP AND MILK.
>> YOU'RE KILLING ME, SMALLS.
STEPHANIE CAME IN AND HER MOUTH
WAS GOING A MILE A MINUTE AND IT
WAS KIND OF ANNOYING.
I'M READY TO GO TO THE DUEL
RIGHT NOW.
I REALLY WANT TO WIN THIS ONE.
I TOLD GOD I'M GOING TO BE
OUT HERE AS LONG AS HE WANTS ME
TO BE OUT HERE SO I'M IN IT FOR
THE LONG HAUL.
>> TREE MAIL!
"HERE YOU GO AGAIN.
BY NOW, YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
SELECT YOUR REDEMPTION VISITORS
AND AGAIN, ONLY CHOOSE TWO."
WHO'S GOING?
>> I'M GOING TO GO.
IF THAT'S OKAY. BECAUSE IT'S MY
TURN AGAIN.
>> CAN I GO WITH YOU, PHILLIP?
>> SURE.
>> SO ROB AND PHILLIP.
>> THERE'S ANOTHER DUEL.
ROB AND I ARE GOING TO GO.
I JUST DON'T TRUST ROB ANYMORE
BECAUSE YESTERDAY ROB AND GRANT
FOUND A CLUE TO AN IDOL AND I
WENT AND I FOLLOWED THEM.
AND WHEN ROB SAW ME HE TRIED TO
HIDE IT.
MIYAMOTO MUSASHI A VERY FAMOUS
JAPANESE HORSE MAN
ONCE WROTE A BOOK CALLED "THE
BOOK OF FIVE RINGS."
AND IN THE BOOK HE SAID WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO WHICH IS SO DIFFICULT
IS LET YOUR ENEMY MOVE FIRST,
AND THAT'S WHERE ROB'S WEAKNESS
IS.
HE LIKES TO BE EXTREMELY
CONTROLLING, AND HE WANTS TO
CONTROL ME.
AND ALL THE OTHER PLAYERS.
BUT NOBODY'S CONTROLLING ME.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BRING YOUR
SHIRT.
>> I DO?
>> PHILLIP WANTED TO GO TO THE
DUEL.
HE'S NOT ALLOWED TO GO WITHOUT A
CHAPERONE SO I HAVE TO
BABY SIT HIS ASS FOR THE DAY.
PHILLIP HAS A BIG MOUTH.
HE LIKES TO TALK AND HE CAN'T BE
TRUSTED.
HE'S DANGEROUS BECAUSE OF HIS
STUPIDITY.
HE'S PROBABLY THE MOST UNAWARE
PERSON I'VE EVER MET IN MY
ENTIRE LIFE.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
MATT WILL BE BATTLING AGAINST
STEPHANIE, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
BOTH TRIBES HAVE SENT MEMBERS TO
WITNESS TODAY'S DUEL.
MATT, YOU SPENT 12 NIGHTS ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU'VE WON FOUR DUELS.
ONCE AGAIN YOU FIND YOURSELF IN
A DO-OR-DIE SITUATION.
READY TO GET TO IT?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE MOST
DIFFICULT ASPECTS OF THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" IS MENTAL FATIGUE.
CONVENIENTLY, TODAY'S DUEL WILL
TEST YOUR MEMORY.
>> PERFECT!
>> Jeff: SCATTERED IN THE ARENA
ARE PAIRS OF MATCHING SYMBOLS.
EACH ROUND YOU'LL FLIP OVER TWO
SYMBOLS.
IF THEY MATCH, YOU SCORE A
POINT.
FIRST TO FIVE STAYS ALIVE, LOSER
IS OUT OF THE GAME FOR GOOD.
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ALL RIGHT, STEPHANIE WON THE
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSOR.
SHE HAS ELECTED TO HAVE MATT GO
FIRST.
YOU'RE FLIPPING OVER TWO
SYMBOLS.
FIRST ROUND IS GOING TO TAKE
SOME LUCK TO GET A MATCH.
MATT FLIPS OVER A SKULL...
AND ANOTHER SKULL.
>> OH, GOD!
>> Jeff: WOW!
>> GOLDEN BOY!
>> Jeff: UNREAL.
WALK OUT ONTO THE COURSE AND
FLIP OVER TWO RANDOM SYMBOLS AND
THEY MATCH.
MATT TAKES AN EARLY ONE-ZIP
LEAD.
STEPHANIE, YOU'RE UP.
STEPHANIE LOOKING FOR THE SAME
KIND OF LUCK.
FLIPS OVER A CROCODILE.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: AND A CROCODILE.
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: REDEMPTION ISLAND GOT
SOMETHING GOING ON OUT HERE.
IT IS 1-1.
MATT IS NOW BACK ON THE COURSE.
MATT FLIPS OVER A CALENDAR.
AND AN EAGLE.
NO MATCH.
STEPHANIE, YOUR TURN.
STEPHANIE FLIPS OVER WAR CLUBS.
AND FIRE.
WE ARE STILL TIED 1-1.
MATT, YOU'RE UP.
MATT FLIPS OVER FIRE.
HAS IT ALREADY BEEN TURNED OVER?
AND IF SO, CAN HE REMEMBER
WHERE?
MATT FLIPS OVER A SECOND FIRE
SYMBOL.
MATT NOW IN THE LEAD 2-1.
STEPHANIE, YOU'RE UP.
STEPHANIE FLIPS OVER A WARRIOR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TEMPLE.
>> Jeff: AND A TEMPLE.
NO MATCH FOR STEPHANIE.
DOOR OPEN FOR MATT TO TAKE A
BIGGER LEAD.
MATT FLIPS OVER THE EAGLE.
GOING TO TAKE A SHOT.
MATT FLIPS OVER ANOTHER EAGLE.
MATT NOW HAS THREE TO
STEPHANIE'S ONE.
WE ARE PLAYING TO FIVE.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: STEPHANIE FLIPS A
TEMPLE.
SHE KNOWS SHE'S SEEN ONE.
WHERE WAS IT?
NICE MATCH FOR STEPHANIE.
MATT LEADS 3-2.
MATT, YOU'RE UP.
MATT FLIPS OVER ONE CANOE,
LOOKING FOR A SECOND CANOE.
AND HE HAS IT.
MATT WITH NOW A VERY BIG LEAD.
MATT HAS 4, STEPHANIE HAS 2.
IT TAKES FIVE TO WIN.
STEPHANIE'S GOT TO GET A MATCH
HERE.
>> WARRIOR.
WHERE WERE YOU?
OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: AND SHE DOES.
STEPHANIE WITH HER THIRD MATCH.
KEEPS HERSELF IN THIS.
>> I'M LOSING MY MIND!
>> Jeff: MATT HAS 4, STEPHANIE
HAS 3.
IT TAKES 5 TO WIN.
MATT COULD DO IT RIGHT HERE.
MATT WITH A CALENDAR.
HAVE WE SEEN A CALENDAR?
>> YES, WE HAVE.
>> Jeff: MATT THOUGHT HE HAD
IT.
HE FLIPS THE HEAD DRESS.
NO MATCH.
DOOR OPEN FOR STEPHANIE NOW.
STEPHANIE QUICKLY FLIPS THE
CALENDAR.
AND THOUGHT SHE HAD IT.
GOT THE WAR CLUBS INSTEAD.
MATT VERY EXCITED NOW.
YOU CAN WIN THE DUEL RIGHT HERE.
MATT FLIPS OVER ONE WAR CLUB.
AND MATT FLIPS OVER THE SECOND
WAR CLUB.
FOR THE FIFTH TIME MATT STAYS
ALIVE, WILL LIVE TO SEE
ANOTHER DAY IN THIS GAME.
( APPLAUSE )
STEPHANIE, WHAT'S THE EMOTIONAL
FEELING RIGHT NOW WHEN YOU WANT
TO PLAY SO BADLY AND NOW YOU ARE
OUT?
>> JUST LEAVING ALTOGETHER
BECAUSE I REALLY WANTED TO BE
HERE UNTIL THE END SO JUST
LETTING GO OF THAT DREAM SUCKS.
I FEEL LIKE THERE ARE PEOPLE
HERE WHO DON'T DESERVE TO BE
HERE.
SARITA IS ONE OF THEM.
RALPH, IF YOU REALLY WANT TO
PLAY THE GAME, YOU NEED TO GET
RID OF HER SOON BECAUSE SHE'S
YOUR WEAKEST LINK.
AND I KNOW YOU THINK DAVE IS
BECAUSE HE VOTED WITH ME FOR
SARITA BUT HE'S THE ONLY GUY WHO
CAN DO PUZZLES.
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE ON THAT
RESPONSIBILITY?
>> IF I GOT TO DO IT, I WILL.
>> Jeff: ROB AND PHILLIP ARE
YOU TEMPTED TO SAY ANYTHING TO
THEM OR ARE THEY ON THEIR OWN?
>> I DON'T KNOW. ROB, LOOK OUT
BECAUSE THEY'RE
GOING TO TRY TO TAKE YOU OUT
LIKE THEY TOOK OUT RUSSELL SO
WATCH YOUR BACK AND I WOULDN'T
TRUST ANYONE ON THEIR TRIBE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> TRY TO WIN THIS GUY BACK.
BUT GOOD LUCK, BECAUSE HE'S BEEN
HERE A LONG TIME.
>> Jeff: STEPHANIE,
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
THIS GAME IS OVER.
YOUR QUEST FOR THE MILLION
DOLLARS DONE.
>> THAT HURTS.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN PUT YOUR BUFF
IN THE FIRE ON YOUR WAY OUT.
MATT, ONCE AGAIN, YOU HAVE
SEIZED THE MOMENT AND LIVED TO
PLAY ANOTHER DAY IN THIS GAME.
PHILLIP, YOU'VE SEEN MATT
COMPETE TWICE NOW.
>> AND I'M VERY IMPRESSED WITH
MATT.
IN THE OLD DAYS OF THE SAMURAI,
THEY HAD SOMETHING CALLED THE
BOCHUTO CODE, WHICH IS WHAT THE
SAMURAI LIVED BY.
WHAT I'VE SEEN IN YOU, YOU ARE
TRULY A SAMURAI WARRIOR.
>> THANK YOU, PHILLIP.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> I APPRECIATE IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MATT, YOU
CAN HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND AND AWAIT YOUR NEXT
OPPONENT.
>> WILL DO, JEFF. YOU KNOW WHERE
TO FIND ME.
>> LITTLE PHILLIP COULDN'T KEEP
HIS MOUTH SHUT, AND I'M TELLING
YOU WHEN THE MERGE IS COMING,
PHILLIP IS READY TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE, AND BY "BIG MOVE" HE MEANS
LET'S GET ROB OUT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SPLIT OUR
TRIBE, BRO.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> WE WANT TO STAY STRONG.
I DON'T WANT ANYBODY TO FEEL
LIKE WE'RE NOT ONE COHESIVE
UNIT, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> OKAY, THEN TELL THEM.
IT'S YOUR CALL.
>> RIGHT WHEN WE GOT BACK,
PHILLIP ASKED ME HOW MUCH IF
ANY I WANTED TO TELL THE TRIBE
OF WHAT WENT ON.
WE'VE BEEN STRAIGHT UP SO FAR.
I'M NOT GOING TO START THAT
GAME, DUDE.
THAT'S NOT HOW I WANT TO PLAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, MAN.
>> I WASN'T UPSET THAT PHILLIP
SUGGESTED WE DON'T SAY ANYTHING
TO THE TRIBE.
IN ACTUALITY, I WAS HOPING FOR
IT, ACTUALLY PRAYING FOR HIM TO
SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT TO ME
SO I COULD JUST USE IT AS
AMUNITION.
AN OPPORTUNITY PRESENTS
ITSELF FOR ME TO
THROW PHILLIP UNDER THE BUS.
YOU GUYS MISSED A CRAZY, CRAZY,
CRAZY DUEL.
>> WHO DID THEY SEND?
>> THEY SENT STEPHANIE.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE FIGURED, YEAH.
>> JEFF WAS QUESTIONING HER, AND
SHE LET IT ALL HANG OUT.
SHE BASICALLY LOOKED AT ME AND
SHE'S LIKE, "ROB, WATCH OUT.
THEY'RE COMING FOR YOU."
I TOOK ALL THIS INFORMATION AND
RELAYED IT ALL TO THE TRIBE
BECAUSE I WANT EVERYBODY ON THE
SAME PAGE.
I WANT EVERYBODY TO KNOW THAT
THE
TARGET'S ON ME SO THAT THEY FEEL
SAFE, NUMBER ONE, AND, NUMBER
TWO, I NEED TO KEEP EVERYBODY
ELSE AGAINST PHILLIP.
RIGHT WHEN WE WERE WALKING ON
THE BEACH HE'S LIKE,
"SO WHAT DO YOU WANT TO TELL
THEM?"
LIKE, HE DIDN'T WANT TO
TELL YOU GUYS.
AND I'M TELLING YOU, FIRST
OPPORTUNITY, THAT'S WHY,
HE'S FLIPPING.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> 100% HE'S FLIPPING BECAUSE WE
LOSE, HE'S GOES TO REDEMPTION.
AND EVERYTHING I JUST TOLD YOU
IS 100% TRUE.
WITH ALL THE ATTENTION FOCUSED
ON PHILLIP
AND EVERYBODY USING HIM AS A
PUNCHING BAG, I'M FREE TO
MANEUVER AND DO WHAT I NEED TO
DO.
>> PHILLIP, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I'M FINE. THANK YOU.
>> EVERYTHING I SUSPECTED ABOUT
PHILLIP IS CONFIRMED.
IF WE LOSE, THERE WON'T BE ANY
BLINDSIDE.
I'LL GO RIGHT UP TO PHILLIP WHEN
HE ASKS ME WHO TO
VOTE FOR AND I'LL SAY, "YOU KNOW
WHAT, PHILLIP?
YOU'RE GOING HOME."
I'LL FRONT-SIDE HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> NOTHING TOO NASTY.
I MEAN NOTHING YOU WOULDN'T--
NOTHING UNEXPECTED.
>> SHE TOLD THE OTHER TEAM TO
PULL HARD, BEAT US.
>> DID SHE REALLY?
>> YES, SHE DID.
>> I DON'T THINK IT WAS
PARTICULARLY EGREGIOUS MANNER.
IT WAS NOTHING OUT OF THE
ORDINARY, NOTHING YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE EXPECTED.
>> HOW IS MATT DOING?
>> HE'S DOING GOOD, BUT HE'S FOR
THE OTHER TEAM.
HE AIN'T GOING TO SWAP SIDES SO
DON'T PLAN ON MATT FAVORING US.
>> YEAH, AND IF YOU FLIP...
>> AFTER THE MERGE...
>> NO ONE RESPECTS A FLIPPER.
>> THEN YOU'RE THE FIRST ONE TO
GO.
>> I THINK DAVID, IF WE MERGE,
HE WOULD JUMP TO THEIR TEAM,
JUST, BAM, LIKE THAT.
I DO BELIEVE.
WELL, HE'S A LAWYER, AND
LAWYERS, YOU GOTTA LOOK AT THEM
THAT WAY.
THEY'RE-- THEY THINK THEY'RE A
LOT BETTER THAN EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> TODAY IS THE DAY TO FISH.
FIRST TIME WE CAUGHT THEM ALL
WAS AFTER A BIG STORM.
>> WHEN THE WATER IS DUMPING OUT
FROM THERE, THAT'S WHEN ALL THE
BAIT FISH WASH OUT FROM THE
RIVER LIKE THE MINNOW AND BRING
THE BIGGER FISH IN TO SHORE.
>> THE 30-YEAR-OLD DAVID
ATTORNEY IS TELLING
THE 45-YEAR-OLD RALPH, MR.
OUTDOORSMAN, THAT WE
OUGHT TO GO FISHING.
SO DAVE IS GETTING TOUGH TO
STOMACH.
>> OKAY, DAVE IS BUGGING ME.
>> YEAH.
>> WE SHOULD GO FISH NOW." YOU
KNOW.
LIKE SHUT UP.
I WANT TO, LIKE, PUNCH HIM IN
THE FACE, HIM AND HIS SMIRK.
IT'S LIKE PICKING HIS WOUND.
>> YOU SEE THAT THE FACE HE
MADE?
>> NO. >> SARITA, SHOW THE FACE
HE MADE.
>> HE'S LIKE YOU GUYS OUGHT TO
BE FISH YOU NOW AND HE'S LIKE...
DAVID'S PERSONALITY IS I FIND
HIM SELFISH AND EGOTISTICAL.
AS MUCH AS HE THINKS HE'S THE
KING OF RIDING THE WILD WATERS
OF "SURVIVOR" HE ISN'T SAVVY AT
THE SOCIAL GAME AT ALL.
>> I'M GUESSING STEVE'S NOT REAL
HAPPY WITH THE FACT THAT I
DECIDED TO DO MY OWN THING LAST
NIGHT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
DAVID, HE MIGHT BE SMART, BUT IT
DON'T TAKE SMART TO WIN THIS
GAME.
IT JUST TAKES SOMEBODY THAT
KNOWS HOW TO MANEUVER AROUND AND
PLAY THE BALL.
WHEN IT COMES OUT HERE IN THE
GENERAL WORLD, SURVIVIN', HE'S
GOT TO GO.
>> HE PROBABLY WILL ONLY EAT
THAT.
DON'T EAT TOO MUCH OF THE CRISPY
STUFF.
I TOLD HIM I WOULD SAVE IT FOR
HIM.
>> THERE'S PLENTY OF IT.
>> YEAH, THERE'S A LOT.
>> I THINK ROB WILL LIKE THE
STUFF ON THE BOTTOM.
>>I WANT ONE SCOOP OF THE
CRISPY, OKAY, JUST ONE.
>> THAT'S ALL ROB IS GOING TO
EAT.
>> BUT I DIDN'T HAVE ONE SCOOP
OF THE CRISPY.
>> WE DIDN'T EITHER.
>> WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY.
>> PHILLIP, REALLY.
>> FORGET IT.
>> YOU CAN HAVE ALL YOU WANT.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T SEE WHERE ONE
SCOOP OF THE CRISPY WOULD
MATTER.
>> IT'S ROB'S SERVING. IT'S
FINE.
>> WHEN WE MAKE IT, GUYS, WE'RE
ALL ENTITLED TO WHATEVER IS
MADE, OKAY, IN EQUAL
PROPORTIONS.
SO IF I WANTED A SCOOP OF CRISPY
AND-- LOOK, I SAW YOU GUYS
GET A SCOOP OF THE CRISPY.
LET'S NOT MAKE A MOUNTAIN OUT OF
A MOLE HILL, FOR CRYING OUT
LOUD.
I'M STANDING RIGHT THERE.
>> HERE, BRO.
>> I DON'T WANT IT.
WHENEVER I-- IT'S LIKE, ROB,
ROB, ROB, ROB, ROB, ROB, ROB!
EVERYBODY LIKES THE BROWN CRISPY
RICE, BUT ROB LIKES IT IN
PARTICULAR.
I WALKED OVER AND SAID, "CAN I
HAVE A LITTLE SCOOP, A SPOONFUL,
A TEASPOONFUL OF THE CRISPY?"
"NO, NO, NO, YOU CAN'T. IT'S ALL
FOR ROB.
EVEN THOUGH THERE'S A FULL
PORTION.
YOU CAN HAVE SOME OF THAT
BUT YOU CAN'T HAVE ANY OF THE
CRISPY."
HOW ASININE IS THAT?
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> I'M SICK AND TIRED OF THE
FACT THAT THEY ACT LIKE BECAUSE
BOSTON ROB IS BOSTON ROB, HE
GETS DEFERENCE TO EVERYTHING.
JUST BECAUSE THEY SLEEP IN HIS
UNDERWEAR EVERY NIGHT-- AND
THAT'S NOT SPEAKING
FIGURATIVELY, THAT'S LITERALLY--
THEY'RE SHARING HIS UNDERWEAR,
THE GIRLS, HIS SOCKS, HIS BED,
AND SO THEY WANT TO PAY HIM
DEFERENCE ON EVERYTHING.
>> LET IT BE KNOWN, THE FIRST
OPPORTUNITY I HAVE TO ELIMINATE
HIM, I WILL.
>> LET HIM EAT THAT.
>> THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
AND HE SAID, "NO. I DON'T WANT
THAT."
>> "DON'T MAKE A MOUNTAIN OUT OF
A MOLE HILL."
>> OH, WELL.
>> ALL DUE RESPECT, I'M A
52-YEAR-OLD MAN, AND THE SENIOR
MEMBER OF THIS TRIBE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WORLD THEY'RE
COMING FROM, BUT IN ANY OTHER
WORLD, I WOULD BE GIVEN THE
DEFERENCE SIMPLY BECAUSE OF MY
AGE.
I'M CERTAINLY ENTITLED TO IT, IF
WE'RE GOING TO CALL THIS A
TRIBE.
BUT INSTEAD I GET THE REDHEADED
STEPCHILD TREATMENT.
>> AM I FEELING PART OF THIS
TRIBE?
HELL NO!
AM I GIVING 100% TO THIS TRIBE,
110% TO THIS TRIBE?
HELL YEAH!
AND I'M SICK OF IT.
I'M NOT QUITTING, I'M HERE TO
STAY, BUT I WANT IT
TO BE ON RECORD THERE IS A
DIVISION IN THIS TRIBE, NOT OF
MY MAKING, OF THEIR MAKING.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> WE ARE!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
WILL TAKE IT
BACK AGAIN, OMETEPE.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
ON MY GO, BOTH TRIBES WILL RACE
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES
WORKING TOGETHER TO COLLECT BAGS
OF BALLS ALONG THE WAY.
ONCE YOU'VE CLEARED ALL THE
OBSTACLES, YOU MUST SHOOT THE
BALLS INTO A BASKET.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET ALL SIX BALLS
IN THEIR BASKET WINS IMMUNITY,
IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THE TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
ANY QUESTIONS?
>> WHAT ARE WE PLAYING FOR?
>> Jeff: IN ADDITION, YOU ARE
PLAYING FOR REWARD.
THE WINNING TRIBE WILL LEAVE
HERE VIA HELICOPTER, TAKEN FOR A
BEAUTIFUL AFTERNOON PICNIC.
YOU'LL ENJOY FRUITS, VEGETABLES,
CHEESE, CHOCOLATE, COOKIES.
YOU'LL HAVE A COOLER FULL OF
ALCOHOLIC AND NON-ALCOHOLIC--
NATALIE-- BEVERAGES.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: WE ARE BACK EVEN.
SIX ON SIX, NOBODY SITTING OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BOTH TRIBES HIT THE HAY HARD.
FLYING OVER IT.
>> COME ON, GET UP!
>> Jeff: SARITA GOING TO WORK
ON THAT FIRST BAG FOR ZAPATERA,
ROB FOR OMETEPE.
ROB WORKING QUICKLY ON THAT
FIRST BAG OF BALLS.
SARITA TAKING A LITTLE TIME FOR
ZAPATERA.
OMETEPE OPENING UP A BIG LEAD
RIGHT NOW.
ZAPATERA REALLY SLOWING DOWN.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA HAS THEIR
FIRST BAG OF BALLS.
>> GO, OMETEPE!
EVERYBODY ON THE MAT!
NOW YOU CAN GO!
PHILLIP NOW CAUGHT UP IN THE
ROPES!
>> YOU'RE GOING UP.
>> UP, UP, UP, UP.
>> Jeff: ROB WORKING ON THAT
BAG OF BALLS AGAIN FOR OMETEPE.
DAVE TAKING OVER FOR ZAPATERA.
DAVID HAS IT FOR ZAPATERA.
ZAPATERA'S PICKED UP A LOT OF
TIME.
ROB STILL STRUGGLING WITH THOSE
BALLS.
GOING THE WRONG WAY!
ROB IS NOW HUNG UP.
OMETEPE HAS THEIR SECOND BAG.
LET'S GO!
OMETEPE HAS LOST TIME.
THEY HAD A BIG LEAD.
>> COME ON!
>> GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY THROUGH THE
CRAWL.
>> BEHIND YOU, PHILLIP!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA WORKING ON
THEIR THIRD AND FINAL BAG OF
BALLS.
PHILLIP AND ROB REALLY DRAGGING
IT FOR OMETEPE.
>> GET UP! GET UP!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP SLOWING DOWN.
ROB AT THE END.
DAVID NOW HAVING TROUBLE WITH
THAT THIRD AND FINAL BAG.
>> GET ME UP! GET ME UP!
>> Jeff: ROB TRYING TO PICK UP
SOME TIME.
DAVID NOW FIGURING IT OUT.
HE'S USING HIS HANDS.
DAVID HAS THE THIRD AND FINAL
BAG FOR ZAPATERA.
THROUGH THE BRICK WALL!
A BIG HIT BY ZAPATERA.
ROB GOTTA KEEP IT MOVING.
ZAPATERA THROUGH THE WALL FIRST!
>> OH, MAN!
>> GET UNTYING, GUYS!
>> Jeff: ROB HAS THE THIRD AND
FINAL BAG FOR OMETEPE.
GRANT THROUGH THE WALL!
EVERYBODY THROUGH THE WALL!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP SMASHES THROUGH
THE BRICKS.
OMETEPE NOW THROUGH THE WALL!
GOTTA GET ALL SIX BALLS IN THE
BASKET.
BOTH TRIBES ALREADY SHOOTING
BALLS NOW.
OMETEPE HAS THEIR FIRST BALL IN.
RALPH NOT HAVING ANY LUCK.
GRANT IS TWO FOR TWO.
GRANT HAS TWO IN FOR OMETEPE.
ZAPATERA WITH ZERO.
ZAPATERA HAS THEIR FIRST BALL.
OMETEPE HAS THEIR THIRD BALL.
ZAPATERA WITH THEIR SECOND BALL.
THEIR THIRD BALL.
WE ARE TIED 3-3.
THERE ARE SIX BALLS TOTAL.
GOTTA GET ALL SIX IN.
ZAPATERA HAS THEIR FOURTH BALL
IN THE NET.
ZAPATERA HAS THEIR FIFTH BALL
IN.
ZAPATERA HAS ONE LEFT.
GRANT PUTS ONE IN FOR OMETEPE.
IT IS 5-4.
BIG REWARD AND BIGGER IMMUNITY
ON THE LINE.
OMETEPE WITH THEIR FIFTH BALL
IN.
BOTH TRIBES HAVE ONE LEFT.
OMETEPE-- OH, IN AND OUT.
GRANT DOES IT!
OMETEPE WINS IMMUNITY AND
REWARD!
>> OH, MAN!
>> SORRY, GUYS.
>> COME ON.
>> WE ALMOST LOST YOU, PHILLIP.
>> WE WERE CLOSE.
>> Jeff: OMETEPE, ONCE AGAIN
CONGRATULATIONS.
ALL RIGHT, ZAPATERA, YOU ARE NOW
DOWN TO SIX MEMBERS.
AFTER TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL,
FIVE.
THINGS ARE GOING FROM BAD TO
WORSE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
OMETEPE, NO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
SHOULD BE A NICE, ENJOYABLE DAY.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
( APPLAUSE )
>> SOME TRIBES ADVANCE BOLDLY.
WEAK TRIBES GROW AGITATED.
BUT SUPERIOR TRIBES, LIKE OURS,
WE FIND A WAY TO WIN.
AND WE DID.
>> THIS IS MY FOURTH TIME ON
"SURVIVOR" AND I'VE BEEN ON A
LOT OF REWARDS, BUT I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT I'VE NEVER DONE IS
LANDED ON TOP OF AN ACTIVE
VOLCANO.
DEFINITELY ONE OF THE
COOLEST EXPERIENCES I'VE EVER
HAD.
>> WHOA!
>> BE CAREFUL.
>> WATCH YOUR FEET, Y'ALL.
>> TAKE A LOOK AT THAT.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WHOO!
>> WOW.
>> HELLO! HELLO!
>> IT'S A HOLE IS THAT GOES
STRAIGHT TO THE CENTER OF THE
EARTH.
>> LITERALLY, I AM SITTING ON
THE EDGE OF A VOLCANO RIGHT NOW.
I'M LOOKING DOWN AT IT RIGHT
NOW, BRO.
I COULD FALL IN HERE AND NEVER
BE HEARD FROM AGAIN.
>> OMETEPE!
>> AND WHAT'S SPECIAL ABOUT IT
IS WE GET TO DO IT AS A TRIBE
TOGETHER AND JUST ENJOY IT.
>> WHAT DO WE GOT?
( CHEERING )
>> WHAT'S IN THERE?
>> CRACKERS.
>> CRACKERS!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH!
I'M ACTUALLY HAVING AN
INCREDIBLE DAY TODAY.
WE HAVE A NUMBERS ADVANTAGE.
AND FOR ME, I HAVEN'T ALWAYS
FELT LIKE I WAS TOTALLY
INCLUSIVE WITH THE GROUP.
BUT TODAY, HAVING A WONDERFUL
MEAL RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> DELICIOUS.
>> MMM!
AND SURVIVING WITH THE TRIBE.
>> WE WON AGAIN!
>> I FIND IT HARD NOT TO BE
TRIBAL IN MY THINKING, COMMUNITY
IN MY THINKING, SO RIGHT NOW I'M
ON TOP OF THE EARTH.
>> WE GOT TO KEEP THIS GOING.
>> COMEBACK KIDS.
>> THEY ARE GOOD BUT WE ARE
BETTER.
>> WHAT'S IN THAT JAR RIGHT
THERE?
>> OH, DUDE, TRY IT.
THEY'RE SO GOOD.
CHOCOLATE SWIRLED IN WAFER.
>> I'VE BEEN ON ENOUGH REWARDS
TO KNOW WHENEVER YOU WIN ONE,
THERE'S GONNA BE A CLUE.
SO IMMEDIATELY IT HITS ME, THE
COOKIES ARE CYLINDRICAL SHAPED.
THE CLUE'S GOT TO BE IN THERE.
>> THOSE WILL MAKE YOUR HEART
STOP.
>> AND SURE ENOUGH IN THE CENTER
IS A CLUE
WRAPPED UP LIKE A COOKIE.
>> DO YOU PUT PESTO ON YOUR
SANDWICH?
>> NO. YOU HAVE SOME?
>> DUDE, IT'S SO GOOD!
BUT IT REALLY DOESN'T EVEN
MATTER WHAT IT SAYS BECAUSE I
ALREADY HAVE THE IDOL, SO...
MIGHT AS WELL JUST THROW IT AWAY
IN THE VOLCANO!
BYE-BYE!
>> THAT CERTAINLY SUCKED.
SO TODAY'S CHALLENGE WAS AN
AWESOME CHALLENGE.
THE OUTCOME COMPLETELY SUCKED.
THAT'S THREE LOSSES IN A ROW,
ALL THREE FOR FOOD.
WE'RE STARVING OUT HERE.
WE'RE TIRED OF GOING TO TRIBAL.
AFTER TONIGHT IT'S GOING TO BE
SIX OF THEM AND FIVE OF US.
NOT A GOOD SITUATION WITH A
LOOMING MERGE.
>> SO WHAT DO WE THINK?
THIS IS PROBABLY THE ONLY TIME
WE'RE REALLY GOING TO HAVE TO
TALK.
>> I WAS THINKING DAVE.
>> ARE YOU GUYS FEELING GOOD
ABOUT LOSING THE PUZZLE MAKER?
I WANT THE TRIBE TO WIN.
>> MICHAEL CAN MORE THAN FILL
HIS SHOES ON THE PUZZLES.
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM DO
ANYTHING TOO OUTSTANDING AT ANY
OF THE CHALLENGES.
>> I FEEL LIKE I CAN DO ANYTHING
DAVE CAN DO AND I FEEL LIKE--
BECAUSE I WOULD SAY KICK ME OFF
IF I FELT LIKE DAVE WAS BETTER
THAN ME.
I JUST DON'T FEEL LIKE HE IS.
I-- I DON'T THINK HE'S GOOD.
TONIGHT IN TRIBAL COUNCIL I'M
GOING TO VOTE FOR DAVID BECAUSE
HE'S A LOOSE CANNON, AND KNOWING
THAT HE VOTED FOR ME LAST TIME,
KNOWING THAT HE DOESN'T TRUST ME
AT ALL, IT DOESN'T REALLY BODE
WELL FOR THE FUTURE.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE ON THE PROGRAM.
I TALKED TO THE OTHER FOUR.
>> YOU HAVE?
>> YEAH.
>> THEY WANT TO GET DAVE?
>> IT'S BESIDE THE POINT.
I DON'T TRUST DAVE NOT TO GET
TOGETHER WITH THEM BEFORE THE
END OF THE DAY AND GET ONE OF US
OFF.
I REALLY DON'T.
I DON'T TRUST DAVE AT ALL.
>> NO, I DON'T EITHER.
>> BUT I DEFINITELY THINK THIS
NEXT ONE IS DAVE.
>> YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
>> I FEEL LIKE DAVID IS GOING TO
HAVE A REALLY GOOD CHANCE OF
BEATING BOY WONDER ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND, WHICH I DON'T WANT TO
SEE HIM COME BACK.
HE'S GOING TO COME BACK LIKE
A HELL ON WHEELS FOR ME, BUT...
THE GAME IS THE GAME.
>> I FEEL A LITTLE BIT MORE
NERVOUS TONIGHT THAN I HAVE IN
THE PAST, PRIMARILY BECAUSE I
DON'T KNOW THAT THE TRIBE HAS
SEEN THE LIGHT IN TERMS OF
KEEPING STRENGTH.
LAST TIME, NOBODY WAS INTERESTED
IN FOCUSING ON STRENGTH OF THE
TRIBE, AND THEY WANTED TO FOCUS
ON TRUST.
IF THAT HAPPENS AGAIN, THERE'S A
DISTINCT POSSIBILITY I AM THE
ONE GOING HOME.
>> HERE COMES DAVE.
GOOD WORK!
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM PICK UP
THAT BIG A PIECE OF LUMBER
SINCE WE'VE BEEN HERE.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
>> WE WERE GOING TO TARGET
DAVID.
BUT SARITA STRUGGLED TODAY.
SHE FUMBLED A COUPLE OF TIMES,
COULDN'T GET THE BAG OPEN,
SHE STARTED PANICKING.
IT JUST WASN'T COMING TOGETHER
FOR HER.
DAVID, ON THE OTHER HAND, REALLY
CAME THROUGH FOR US.
>> FOR THE STRENGTH OF THE TRIBE
IN CHALLENGES, WE THINK WE'VE
GOT TO KEEP DAVE.
>> REALLY?
>> IN MY EYES, YOU KNOW, I DON'T
TRUST DAVID.
>> I DON'T TRUST HIM AT ALL.
>> I LOVE SARITA, I THINK SHE'S
GREAT BUT SHE'S
BEEN SUPER, SUPER WEAK AT EVERY
CHALLENGE.
SHE TENDS TO GET FLUSTERED AND
FREAKED OUT A LITTLE BIT.
SHE JUST DOESN'T HAVE THAT
INTESTINAL FORTITUDE, YOU KNOW.
SHE'S ABSOLUTE THE WEAKEST AT
THIS POINT.
TONIGHT WE HAVE TWO OPTIONS--
DAVID OR SARITA.
SARITA VERY LOYAL, VERY
TRUSTWORTHY.
HOWEVER, IN CHALLENGES SHE'S
VERY FLUSTERED AND NOT VERY
STRONG.
DAVID, ON THE OTHER HAND, HE'S A
THINKER.
HE'S VERY SMART.
I THINK HE'LL HELP US GET
THROUGH FUTURE CHALLENGES WITH
PUZZLES.
HOWEVER, HE'S A LITTLE BIT
HARDER TO TRUST, AND IF WE END
UP MERGING SOME TIME SOON, WHO
DO WE WANT TO HAVE WITH US AT
THE MERGE?
IT'S A TOTAL CATCH-22 AT THIS
POINT.
EITHER WE HAVE A LOYAL TRIBE OR
WE HAVE A TAD BIT STRONGER
TRIBE.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE IN A BIT OF A
TAILSPIN AND WE HAVE A COUPLE
THOUSAND FEET BEFORE WE HIT THE
DECK AND CRASH AND BURN SO WE
NEED TO FIGURE A WAY OUT OF THIS
TAILSPIN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, RALPH, YOU
TELL ME-- WHAT HAS HAPPENED TO
ZAPATERA?
>> JEFF, IT WAS PRETTY CLOSE
TODAY.
WE WAS AHEAD, BUT WHEN IT GOT TO
THE BALLS...
>> CAN I PIPE IN?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: DAVID, FINISH THIS
SENTENCE, "EXCUSES ARE FOR..."?
>> LOSERS.
>> I'M A LOSER THEN.
>> Jeff: JULIE, THERE IS ONE
GLARING STAT.
SINCE YOU THREW THE CHALLENGE TO
GET RID OF RUSSELL YOU HAVE LOST
THE NEXT THREE OF FOUR
CHALLENGES.
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
IT IS BAD KARMA.
AT THE TIME, JEFF, WE THOUGHT
OUR TRIBE WAS WAY STRONGER THAN
THE OTHER TRIBE AND WE THOUGHT
WE COULD SPARE TO THROW ONE
CHALLENGE AND WE STILL FEEL LIKE
WE'RE STRONGER THAN THE OTHER
TRIBE.
>> Jeff: DAVID, MAYBE THE
PROBLEM ISN'T THAT YOU'RE NOT AS
STRONG AS THE OTHER TRIBE.
MAYBE THE PROBLEM IS YOU'RE JUST
NOT AS COHESIVE.
>> I THINK THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
THE PROBLEM IS.
IT'S A LACK OF UNITY HERE.
WHEN WE WERE BANDED TOGETHER
AGAINST RUSSELL THAT WAS
SOMETHING WE ALL HAD A SIMILAR
GOAL TOWARDS.
BUT IF YOU LOOK AT THE OTHER
TRIBE, IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE ALL
FRIENDS.
THEY'RE ALL SITTING THERE
LAUGHING, GIGGLING, AND HAVING A
GOOD TIME.
IT WOULD SEEM TO ME THAT'S A
COMPONENT OF THEIR DAILY LIFE.
>> Jeff: RALPH, DOES THAT RING
TRUE TO YOU, HOW IMPORTANT IT IS
THAT THE ENTIRE GROUP BE
COHESIVE?
>> WELL, FIRST, JEFF, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT "COHESIVE" MEANS.
>> Jeff: WELL IN YOUR JOB YOU
MANAGE A GROUP OF GUYS, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE
A DOZEN GUYS WHO ARE REALLY
STRONG BUT DIDN'T GET ALONG VERY
WELL OR A DOZEN GUYS THAT MAYBE
AREN'T THAT STRONG BUT WORK
WELL AS A UNIT.
>> I DISAGREE.
>> Jeff: IT'S A QUESTION.
WHICH WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE?
>> I WOULD RATHER HAVE ONES THAT
ARE STRONGER BECAUSE IF THEY DO
GET ALONG, YAK, YAK, YAK, YAK.
>> I RESPECTFULLY DISAGREE.
I THINK ANY COACH WOULD RATHER
HAVE A GROUP THAT GETS ALONG.
AND I REALLY BELIEVE THAT WE'RE
ALL WORKING TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: KRISTA WOULD
DISAGREE, STEPHANIE WOULD
DISAGREE, AND FROM WHAT I SEE
RECENTLY BETWEEN DAVID AND
SARITA, DAVID WOULD PROBABLY
DISAGREE.
>> THAT'S WHY KRISTA AND
STEPHANIE ARE GONE.
THEY WERE THE DISSENTERS AMONG
THE GROUP.
DAVID MAY DISAGREE BUT I KNOW
THAT WE FEEL WE'RE STRONGER.
>> Jeff: DAVID, YOU HAVE BEEN
PRETTY VOCAL IN YOUR SUPPORT OF
KRISTA AND STEPHANIE.
ARE YOU CONCERNED THAT MAY NOW
PUT THE TARGET ON YOU?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
STEPHANIE'S REFUSAL TO VOTE WITH
THE TRIBE AND INSTEAD VOTING
WITH KRISTA TIPPED THE SCALES
AGAINST HER ULTIMATELY.
THE FACT THAT I DID THE SAME
THING AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL
CONCERNS ME BUT I GAVE STEPHANIE
MY WORD.
AND I'M NOT GONNA JUMP BACKWARDS
AT THAT POINT.
>> Jeff: SARITA, DAVID MAKES
THE ARGUMENT BY KEEPING HIS WORD
HE IS ACTUALLY SHOWING HE'S
LOYAL.
>> THAT DOESN'T REALLY FLY WITH
ME
JUST BECAUSE I TRUSTED IN THE
SIX.
>> I TRUSTED IN THE SIX AND I
DON'T HAVE ANY INDIVIDUAL TRUST
IN YOU.
>> I WAS SURPRISED WHEN DAVID
VOTED FOR ME LAST WEEK.
I THOUGHT THE SIX WAS STRONG AND
NO MATTER WHAT DIFFERENCES WE
HAD I WOULD NEVER HAVE WRITTEN
HIS NAME DOWN BECAUSE I DO HONOR
MY ALLIANCES.
BUT THEN HE YELLED AT ME A
COUPLE OF TIMES
AND GOT ME IN MY FACE AND THAT'S
NOT A PERSON I CAN TRUST.
IT DOESN'T MEAN THE SIX CHANGE,
IT MEANT THAT I WASN'T
GONNA BE THICK AS THIEVES WITH
DAVID.
>> CARRY ON AFTER THE SIX SO
THERE WAS BASICALLY NO ALLIANCE
BETWEEN THE TWO OF US BUT SHE
WAS STILL WILLING TO WORK WITH
ME WITHIN THE SIX.
>> WE HAD AN AGREEMENT FOR THE
SIX AND WE HAD A HIERARCHY OF
WHAT WE WERE GOING TO DO, AND HE
FLIPPED ON THAT AND DECIDED TO
ALIGN WITH STEPHANIE.
>> I DIDN'T FLIP ON ANY
HIERARCHY.
I DID WHAT I THOUGHT WAS BEST
FOR THE TRIBE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: BUT TONIGHT, THINGS
ARE DIFFERENT BECAUSE THERE IS
NO STEPHANIE AND THERE IS NO
KRISTA.
>> AND MY NAME WAS WRITTEN DOWN.
>> Jeff: SO NOW YOU'RE GUNNING
FOR DAVID.
>> UM...
>> OF COURSE SHE IS.
IT'S OBVIOUS.
THAT QUESTION DOESN'T EVEN NEED
TO BE ASKED.
IF SHE THINKS I'VE BETRAYED THE
ALLIANCE OF COURSE SHE'S GOING
TO GO AFTER ME.
I DIDN'T PLEAD MY CASE TO ANYONE
THIS AFTERNOON.
EVERYONE HAS THEIR MIND MADE UP.
WHETHER IT'S ME OR HER, SO BE
IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELL THIS
GROUP OF SIX IS ABOUT TO BE
BROKEN UP.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
JULIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> I WAS ALWAYS HONEST WITH YOU,
AND YOU BETRAYED ME.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE YOU
HAVE A LOT OF GREAT QUALITIES.
>> I HOPE YOU LOVE REDEMPTION
ISLAND AS MUCH AS I LOVE WRITING
YOUR NAME DOWN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SARITA.
DAVID.
TWO VOTES DAVID, ONE VOTE
SARITA.
WE'RE TIED-- TWO VOTES SARITA,
TWO VOTES DAVID.
SARITA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES SARITA, TWO
VOTES DAVID, ONE VOTE LEFT.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,"
SARITA.
>> OH, MY GOD. >> Jeff: NEED TO
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> I WISH I'D BROUGHT MY STUFF.
>> DON'T GET TOO CONFIDENT.
>> Jeff: SARITA, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
BYE, GUYS.
>> Jeff: YOU WILL HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
WELL, IF THERE WAS ANY QUESTION
AS TO WHETHER OR NOT THIS IS ONE
COHESIVE GROUP, TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL CERTAINLY ANSWERED IT.
NO.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> THAT CUT MY FOOT PRETTY
BADLY.
>> Jeff: AN INJURY HURTS
MATT'S CHANCES IN THE MOST
IMPORTANT DUEL YET.
THE WINNER OF TODAY'S DUEL WILL
GO BACK IN THE GAME.
AND ROB HEARS THE THREE WORDS
THAT COULD PUT AN END TO HIS
DOMINANCE-- WE ARE MERGED.
>> THIS IS A WHOLE NEW GAME.
>> I CAN SEE PARANOIA GETTING TO
HIM.
>> I KNOW THEY'RE COMING AFTER
ME.
>> IN THE END, DAVID WON OUT,
BASICALLY SAYING HE WAS THE
STRONGER, WHICH IS FINE.
WHAT THEY DON'T REALIZE IS YOU
DON'T ALWAYS PICK THE STRONGER,
ESPECIALLY NOW THAT YOU'RE
GETTING DOWN.
YOU WANT SOMEONE WHO MAYBE WILL
NOT WIN INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
THEY WANT TO MAKE THE MOST
ROBUST FOOTBALL TEAM THEY CAN
POSSIBLY MAKE.
GOD LOVE THEM FOR IT.