>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": 16 CASTAWAYS WERE
AIRLIFTED TO A REMOTE BEACH
IN NICARAGUA.
WELCOME TO SURVIVOR!
WHERE THEY WERE SURPRISED BY TWO
OF SURVIVOR'S
MOST VILLAINOUS RIVALS.
>> BOSTON ROB!
>> Jeff: BOSTON ROB AND
RUSSELL HANTZ.
THESE TWO OFFER 156 DAYS OF
"SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE.
ROB, YOU JOIN OMETEPE.
RUSSELL HANTZ, YOU JOIN
ZAPATERA.
COME ON, RUSSELL, LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: THERE IS ONE MORE
TWIST.
WHEN YOU ARE VOTED OUT, YOU WILL
NOT GO HOME.
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: INSTEAD YOU WILL BE
SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHERE
YOU WILL LIVE ALONE.
WHEN THE NEXT PERSON JOINS YOU
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND, THE TWO OF
YOU WILL SQUARE OFF IN A DUEL.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: THE WINNER STAYS.
THE LOSER IS OUT OF THE GAME
FOR GOOD.
AT THE ZAPATERA TRIBE, RUSSELL
LOST NO TIME ALIGNING WITH THE
PRETTY YOUNG TRIBEMATE.
>> WHEN WE GET TO THE MERGE,
IT WILL BE OVER.
>> DONE.
>> Jeff: BUT EVERYONE ELSE
IMMEDIATELY FIGURED OUT WHAT
RUSSELL WAS UP TO.
>> AT THIS POINT, GET RUSSELL
GONE AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> Jeff: AT THE OMETEPE TRIBE,
ALMOST EVERYONE FELL UNDER
BOSTON ROB'S CHARISMATIC SPELL.
>> IT'S SUCH A BLESSING TO HAVE
ROB HERE.
WE MIGHT AS WELL CALL IT
CAMP HARMONY RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: BUT KRISTINA DECIDED
ROB WAS TOO DANGEROUS TO KEEP
AROUND SO SHE JOINED FORCES WITH
PHILLIP AND FRANCESCA
TO GET HIM OUT.
>> I'M TOTALLY ON BOARD.
>> OKAY, COOL.
>> Jeff: AND WHEN KRISTINA
FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL,
HER PLAN SEEMED FOOLPROOF.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL PHILLIP TURNED
ON HIS ALLIES AND SPILLED THE
BEANS TO HIS ENTIRE TRIBE.
>> YOU AND FRANCESCA APPROACHED
ME TO GO ALONG WITH THEM BECAUSE
SHE HAS AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
JEFF, I'M A FORMER
SPECIAL AGENT.
>> ARE YOU A CRAZY PERSON.
>> Jeff: FRANCESCA WAS
VOTED OUT.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
BUT YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO
RE-ENTER THIS GAME.
TAKE YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> AH, GOOD TIMES.
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT, IT'S BEEN
KIND OF DOWNHILL.
NOW REDEMPTION ISLAND, MY MIND
IS JUST RACING.
I DON'T THINK I'M GOING
TO SLEEP TONIGHT.
I DON'T REALLY SEE HOW I CAN
SLEEP TONIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO.
LIFE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND: YOU
WILL HAVE BASIC SUPPLIES TO HELP
YOU MAINTAIN YOUR WORLD HERE.
YOU WILL RECEIVE A RATION OF
RICE EACH DAY AND PLENTY OF
DRINKING WATER.
AT A CERTAIN POINT, THE
REMAINING PERSON ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND WILL RE-ENTER THE GAME
AND RESUME THEIR QUEST FOR THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE
MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
GOOD LUCK.
TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS CRAZY.
I THOUGHT THAT IT WOULD BE, BUT
NOT LIKE THAT.
PHILLIP TOTALLY JUST FLIPPED OUT
AND SAID A LOT OF THINGS.
AND I CERTAINLY WASN'T EXPECTING
TO BE VOTED OUT,
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I HAVE A SECOND CHANCE.
HERE I AM ON MY ISLAND.
PLEASE, GOD,
TELL ME I HAVE FLINT.
OH, WONDERFUL.
WONDERFUL, WONDERFUL.
OKAY.
I THINK THAT COMING TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND COULD BE THE
BEST THING FOR MY GAME BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, I WAS ON GOOD TERMS
WITH EVERYONE IN MY TRIBE, BUT I
WAS NOT PART OF, LIKE,
THE CORE ALLIANCE.
SO IF I CAN MAKE IT OUT HERE AND
COME BACK AT SOME POINT IN THE
GAME WHEN THINGS ARE CHANGING
BECAUSE THINGS
ARE CHANGING EVERY DAY,
I COULD STILL WIN
"SURVIVOR."
LET'S SEE IF I CAN START A FIRE
ALL BY MYSELF.
I'M ACTUALLY NOT SAD AT ALL THAT
I'M NOT GOING BACK TO MY CAMP
BECAUSE I'D MUCH RATHER BE HERE
THAN STILL BE BACK IN THE GAME
WITH PHILLIP
AND ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
OH, GOD.
>> THAT WAS-- THAT TURNED-- THAT
WHOLE THING--
>> THAT WAS ONE OF THE WILDEST
TRIBAL COUNCILS I'VE EVER BEEN
A PART OF.
>> REALLY.
>> THEY WERE YELLING
AT EACH OTHER.
>> IT WAS PRETTY WILD.
>> THE TRIBAL COUNCIL DIDN'T GO
EXACTLY AS I HAD HOPED.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN PERFECT IF I
HADN'T MENTIONED ANYTHING TO
PHILLIP AT ALL ABOUT HAVING THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I LOST THE BATTLE, BUT IT'S NOT
THE END OF THE GAME.
I STILL HAVE THE IDOL IN MY
POSSESSION, AND I AM SO GRATEFUL
I DID NOT PLAY THAT THING.
I'M SO HAPPY.
>> CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> STEP OVER HERE, PLEASE.
>> I KNOW FOR A FACT THAT
KRISTINA AND PHILLIP WERE LYING
BUT IT DOESN'T TAKE A GENIUS
F.B.I. MAN TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
ALL YOU HAD TO DO WAS LOOK AT
THEIR FACES AND WATCH
THEIR LIPS MOVING.
>> I ALMOST GOT DUPED TONIGHT,
TODAY.
>> YEAH.
>> I WANT TO SAY SOME THINGS
FROM MY HEART TO YOU.
UNTIL I GO TO REDEMPTION YOU OWN
MY VOTE.
>> THANKS.
>> WHEN I COME BACK, I'M A
COMPETITOR LIKE I SAID.
>> THIS GUY PHILLIP, F.B.I.,
WHATEVER SPECIAL AGENT, HE IS A
PIECE OF WORK.
HE TOLD ME THAT I OWN HIS VOTE
FOR THE REST OF THE TIME HE'S
HERE UNTIL HE GOES
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> I WANT TO PLAY TO THE LEVEL
OF INTEGRITY THAT WHEN I SAY
SOMETHING, IT MEANS SOMETHING.
THAT'S REALLY--
>> I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S
DELUSIONAL.
I THINK HE'S A GOOD-HEARTED GUY.
I DO.
JUST MIGHT NOT ALL BE THERE.
LET IT BE A LESSON TO YOU--
GOVERNMENT JOBS, STRESSFUL.
>> LET'S GET TO SIX AND THEN WE
CAN PLAY ALL THE STRATEGY
WE WANT.
BUT, LIKE, LET'S JUST GET
TO SIX FIRST.
I'M NOT MAKING ANY BONES
ABOUT IT.
THIS IS MY ALLIANCE.
THAT'S IT.
>> AND NOW ONCE WE KNOW WHO
WE'RE VOTING FOR, NOW WE KNOW WE
DON'T TELL ANYBODY ELSE.
>> VOTE PHILLIP.
PHILLIP'S GONE.
WITH THE EXCEPTION OF PHILLIP'S
LITTLE TWIST WHERE HE DECIDED TO
OUT FRANCESCA, THINGS WENT
PRETTY MUCH ACCORDING TO PLAN.
IT SEEMS AS IF THIS GROUP OF
PLAYERS KNOWS HOW
TO FOLLOW DIRECTIONS.
PHILLIP DID IT TO HIMSELF.
HE'S AN IDIOT.
JUST TRY TO WIN A COUPLE OF
CHALLENGES BEFORE WE HAVE
TO LET HIM GO.
>> I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
>> RIGHT THERE.
LOOK AT THAT.
JUST MISSED HIM.
WHEN I WENT HUNTING FOR THE
CRABS, YOU KNOW, YOU FIND
YOURSELF GOING BACK
TO THAT PRIMAL STATE.
THERE'S A PART OF THAT COMES TO
A PLACE WHERE YOU REALIZE HERE
IN SURVIVOR, YOU ARE GOING TO BE
TESTED IN SO MANY WAYS.
>> THE FINE SPECIMEN IS CREEPING
UP ON HIS PRIZE.
>> HE HAS HIS PINK SHORTS ON.
>> THERE TRAPS THE CRABS.
>> WHEN I REVEALED TO THE GIRLS
THAT I WAS A FORMER
FEDERAL AGENT,
IT WAS DESIGNED TO LET THE GIRLS
KNOW THAT I AM A TRUSTWORTHY
PERSON AND AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
LAST NIGHT, FRANCESCA MALIGNED
MY CHARACTER AND I WAS
DEFINITELY IMPACTED EMOTIONALLY
BECAUSE ONE OF THE THINGS ABOUT
ME IS THAT I LOVE MY COUNTRY.
HAVING WORN THE UNIFORM THAT I
SWORE THAT I WAS PREPARED TO--
TO PROTECT AND DEFEND, TO HAVE
HER TRY TO TAKE SOME OF THAT
PRIDE I HAVE, AND HAVING SERVED
AS A SPECIAL AGENT AND EARNED
THE RIGHT TO BE CALLED
"TRUSTWORTHY," IT HURT ME.
IT MADE ME ANGRY.
I HAD LOTS OF EMOTIONAL FEELINGS
GOING ON.
GOT ONE!
AND I THINK THE BEST LESSON I
GOT LAST NIGHT FOR ME PERSONALLY
BESIDES THE GAME ASPECT WAS I
STILL LOVE PHILLIP SHEPPARD.
HE'S A GOOD GUY.
AND THAT'S OKAY.
KILLED ONE WITH A STONE, BABY.
>> YOU ARE A LEGEND, SIR.
>> THESE FOOLS THAT I'M DEALING
WITH, THEY AIN'T TOO BRIGHT.
AND POOR OLD RALPH.
THAT DUDE MIGHT BE THE DUMBEST
PLAYER TO EVER PLAY.
HE MIGHT BE THE DUMBEST PLAYER
PERSON THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
IT'S PITIFUL.
BUT I'VE GOT A GOOD PLAYER
WITH ME.
STEPHANIE'S A GOOD PLAYER.
NOW ALL I NEED IS KRISTIN.
THREE WORKED FOR ME BEFORE.
I BELIEVE IT JUST MIGHT WORK
FOR ME AGAIN.
OKAY, YOU KNOW
WHAT WE NEED TO DO?
NEXT CHALLENGE, FOR REWARD,
THERE MIGHT BE A CLUE FOR THE
HIDDEN IDOL.
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO DO
IS YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO LOOK
EVERYWHERE.
I'M GOING TO TELL STEPHANIE
THE SAME THING.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M GOING TO START LOOKING
FOR THE IDOL WITHOUT THE CLUE
TODAY.
SO-- I COME TO REALIZE THAT I
CAN TRUST NOBODY BUT MY PEOPLE.
KRISTA AND STEPHANIE, MY
ALLIANCE, MY TWO GIRLS.
THAT'S IT.
I BELIEVE THAT'S ALL I HAVE
RIGHT NOW.
THEY HAVE ONE SOMEWHERE
FOR SURE.
LOOK IN TREES.
RIGHT NOW, I HAVE TO GO ALL OUT.
SO MY PLAN IS FIND THE IDOL.
YEAH, YOU'VE SEEN ME PLAY
BEFORE.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SEEN?
YOU SEEN ME FINDING IDOLS.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SEEN.
IT'S HOW I PLAY THIS GAME.
>> RUSSELL IS RUNNING AROUND
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
>> YEAH.
I WAS PICKING UP A FEW ROCKS,
AND I JUST HAPPENED TO LOOK IN
THAT STUMP, AND I THOUGHT WHAT'S
THAT ROCK DOING IN THERE AND I
PULLED IT OUT
AND THERE LAY THE IDOL.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE I FOUND IT
THAT EASY.
RUSSELL THOUGHT HE WAS KING
AT FINDING THEM IDOLS.
HE KNOWS WHERE THEY'RE AT.
SO, RUSSELL,
EAT YOUR HEART OUT, MAN.
OH, BABY, YOU'RE MINE.
>> IT GIVES ME A CERTAIN PEACE
KNOWING I'M NOT OUT HERE
BY MYSELF, YOU KNOW.
I WAS PRAYING GOD WOULD PUT ME
IN AN ALLIANCE LIKE THE KIND HE
WANTED ME TO BE IN.
I'M PRETTY THRILLED.
>> ME TOO, ME, TOO.
>> HE'S SO HARD CORE.
YOU NEED TO COME HANG OUT
IN WISCONSIN.
>> WILL YOU?
MATT IS REALLY CUTE.
GOOD TO LOOK AT, BUT, YOU KNOW
WE'RE JUST-- WE'RE CLOSE, AND I
THINK WE HAVE A LITTLE BIT
OF LOYALTY GOING ON.
ACTUALLY, YEAH.
>> MATT'S TRYING TO PLAY THE
GOOD GUY, BUT ANDREA KNOWS WHAT
SHE WANTS, AND IF SHE CAN HAVE
HER LITTLE PUPPY DOG ALONG FOR
THE RIDE, SHE'S GOING
TO WALK HIM.
SHE'S GOING TO WALK HIM ALL OVER
THIS ISLAND, AND FOR ME, THAT'S
NOT GOOD BECAUSE I KNOW HOW
STRONG A PAIR CAN BE
IN THIS GAME.
LIKE AMBER AND I.
BUT NOW I'M THINKING ABOUT WHO
I'M GOING TO SIT NEXT TO
AT THE END.
HOW'S THE VIBE WITH HIM?
EVERYBODY GOOD.
>> YEAH, FOR SURE.
>> WHAT ABOUT MATTY AND ANDREA?
>> I THINK THEY'RE DANGEROUS.
>> MATT'S LOOKING FOR A WAY TO
GET FAR WITH ANDREA.
>> YEAH.
>> FOR SURE.
I MEAN, FOR SURE, 100%,
I KNOW THAT GAME.
I PLAYED THAT GAME WITH AMBER.
YOU KNOW.
I THINK NATALIE'S A PERFECT
PARTNER AT THIS POINT, BUT IT'S
GOING TO BE HARD, THOUGH.
IT'S LIKE, LITERALLY, PICKING
THE GIRL UP, PUTTING HER ON MY
BACK, AND I'M GOING TO DRAG YOUR
ASS TO THE END, AND HOPEFULLY
THEY'RE GOING TO GIVE IT TO ME
AT THE END.
THE OPTIONS, AS I SEE IT, IF WE
LOSE THE NEXT ONE, WE HAVE TO
GET RID OF PHILLIP OR WE HAVE TO
GET RID OF ANDREA IN ORDER TO
KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG.
MATT WILL GET HURT BY IT, BUT WE
DON'T HAVE TO TELL MATT,
YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT?
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
>> I'M GOING TO MAKE BIG MOVES,
BUT I REALLY TRUST ROB, AND I
THINK MAKING BIG MOVES ALONG
WITH HIM WILL BE SMART.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ZAPATERA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW OMETEPE TRIBE.
FRANCESCA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WHAT?
>> SHE WAS STRONG.
>> THEY'RE DUMB.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
RALPH, I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
>> I'LL GET IT BACK.
>> Jeff: OH, YEAH.
>> SEE YOU TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, DOES THAT
INSPIRE YOU WHEN SOMEBODY THROWS
THAT IN YOUR FACE AND SAYS,
"THIS BABY IS COMING BACK
WITH US."
>> IT BRINGS OUT THE ANIMAL
IN ME.
I WILL OUTLAST ANY MAN
OVER THERE.
>> Jeff: WHAT ABOUT THE WOMEN?
>> THAT'S ANOTHER DAY.
WE'LL SEE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FOR
TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING
TO SWIM OUT TO A PLATFORM, CLIMB
TO THE TOP, SMASH A TILE, AND
RETRIEVE A KEY,
THEN THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE RETRIEVED ALL FIVE
KEYS, ONE PERSON WILL USE THOSE
KEYS TO OPEN A BOX
AND RETRIEVE A BALL.
THE REMAINING TWO TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL USE THAT BALL
TO BREAK FIVE TILES.
FIRST TRIBE TO BREAK ALL FIVE
TILES WINS IMMUNITY, IS SAFE
FROM THE VOTE, AND AVOIDS
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING
FOR REWARD.
FISHING GEAR.
>> OH, FISHING STUFF!
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT A MASK,
FINS.
YOU'VE GOT LINE, HOOK, SINKER.
YOU'VE GOT A FISHING SPEAR.
>> SWEET!
>> Jeff: BIG REWARD.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT, WILL
BE SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND,
AND WILL HAVE TO FACE OFF
AGAINST FRANCESCA IN A DUEL.
ZAPATERA, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
TRIBEMEMBER.
SITTING ONE PERSON OUT.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> DAVID.
>> Jeff: DAVID, TAKE A SPOT
ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, GIVE YOU
A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD AND IMMUNITY,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BRANDT AND STEVE
IN THE WATER FIRST.
BRANDT ALMOST GETS THERE JUST
ON HIS DIVE ALONE.
GRANT UP QUICKLY.
GRANT GETS THE KEY.
>> HE'S GOOD!
( APPLAUSE )
>> BRING IT HOME!
>> Jeff: GRANT IS BACK.
ASHLEY'S IN THE WATER.
>> COME ON, ASHLEY!
>> Jeff: SARITA'S IN THE WATER.
ASHLEY NOW WITH A LEAVE
ON OMETEPE.
SIRITA TRYING TO PICK UP
SOME GROUND.
ASHLEY WITH A NICE SMASH
AND GRABS THE KEY.
>> YEAH, WAY TO GO!
>> Jeff: SARITA SMASHES
HER TILE.
ASHLEY IS BACK.
MATT IS IN THE WATER.
SARITA TRYING TO GET BACK.
MATT ALREADY TO THE PLATFORM.
SARITA'S BACK.
JULIE'S IN THE WATER
FOR ZAPATERA.
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> Jeff: MATT HAS THE THIRD
KEY FOR OMETEPE.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: ANDREA WITH A BELLY
FLOP IN THE WATER.
JULIE SMASHES A TILE.
JULIE'S GOT TO GET THE KEY NOW.
ANDREA IN THE AIR.
>> RIGHT THERE!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE WITH
A ONE-KEY LEAD.
RUSSELL IN THE WATER
FOR ZAPATERA.
BOSTON ROB NOW GOING
FOR THAT FIFTH KEY.
FOR OMETEPE.
>> YOU GOT IT!
>> GO, RUSSELL!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL SMASHES
THE TILE.
AND COMES UP WITH THE KEY
IN HAND.
>> COME ON, ROB!
>> Jeff: ROB SMASHES THE TILE
AND COMES UP WITH THE KEY
IN HAND.
MIKE IN THE WATER FOR ZAPATERA.
ROB BACK WITH THE FIFTH KEY.
NATALIE NOW WORKING
ON THOSE LOCKS.
MIKE HAS THE FIFTH
AND FINAL KEY FOR ZAPATERA.
ZAPATERA WAS BEHIND
BUT THEY HAVE CAUGHT UP.
STEPHANIE NOW WORKING
ON THE LOCKS.
THERE ARE FIVE KEYS.
ONLY THREE LOCKS.
STEPHANIE HAS THE FIRST LOCK
UNDONE FOR ZAPATERA.
>> SPIN IT BACK THE OTHER WAY.
THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: NATALIE HAS HER FIRST
LOCK UNDONE.
STEPHANIE HAS THE SECOND LOCK
UNDONE FOR ZAPATERA.
NATALIE HAS THE SECOND
LOCK OPEN.
>> STEPHANIE HAS ALL THREE
LOCKS OPEN.
SHE'S GOT THE BOX OPEN.
THERE'S ONE BALL.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: NATALIE HAS THE THIRD
LOCK OPEN.
>> HAND ME THE BALL.
HAND ME THE BALL.
>> Jeff: IT IS RALPH
AND PHILLIP TOSSING BALLS.
PHILLIP BREAKS THE FIRST TILE
FOR OMETEPE.
RALPH BREAKS THE FIRST TILE
FOR ZAPATERA.
>> LET'S GO, PHILLIP,
YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: RALPH BREAKS THE
SECOND TILE FOR ZAPATERA.
RALPH BREAKS THE THIRD TILE
FOR ZAPATERA.
LET'S SEE THAT ANIMAL, PHILLIP.
>> COME ON!
COME ON, BABY, HERE WE GO!
>> Jeff: RALPH BREAKS THE
FOURTH TILE FOR ZAPATERA.
ONE MORE TILE AND THEY WIN
IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
>> DAGGONE IT!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE BREAKS
THEIR SECOND TILE.
RALPH JUST MISSES.
OMETEPE BREAKS THEIR THIRD TILE.
>> YOU GOT THIS, RALPH,
YOU GOT IT.
>> DANG!
>> Jeff: RALPH ALL AROUND THAT
LAST TILE BUT CAN'T BREAK IT.
OMETEPE BREAKS
THEIR FOURTH TILE.
IT IS 4-4.
ONE TILE LEFT.
RALPH BREAKS THE FIFTH TILE!
ZAPATERA WINS REWARD
AND IMMUNITY.
>> WHAT IS HE DOING?
MATT'S SHAKING THE OPPOSITION'S
HAND AFTER WE LOST
THE CHALLENGE.
THAT'S DESPICABLE.
WHEN JUST GOT OUR ASSES KICKED,
NOT ONCE, BUT TWICE,
BACK TO BACK.
I'M NOT GOING EVER TO THE OTHER
TEAM AND GIVING THEM HUGS
AND KISSES.
ZAPATERA YOU SAID YOU WOULD WIN
IT AGAIN AND YOU DID.
>> THANK YOU!
GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA COME COLLECT
YOUR REWARD AND HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
ALL RIGHT, OMETEPE,
TRIBAL COUNCIL ONCE AGAIN.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
THAT PERSON WILL GO DIRECTLY TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL
JOIN FRANCESCA, AND YOU WILL
COMPETE IN A DUEL.
IT WILL BE YOUR LAST CHANCE TO
SAVE YOURSELF IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> HOLY CRAP.
>> IT'S GETTING READY TO POUR.
>> WE JUST WIN THE CHALLENGE, SO
I GRAB THE BASKET BECAUSE I KNOW
IF THERE'S GOING TO BE A CLUE,
IT'S GOING TO BE IN THAT BASKET.
AND AS I'M WALKING, I SEE A CLUE
SLIPPING OUT OF THE FLIPPERS.
I DON'T SAY ANYTHING TO ANYBODY.
I JUST GRAB THE CLUE
AND PUT IT IN MY HAND.
I KNOW THIS GAME.
THIS ISN'T MY FIRST RODEO.
>> RALPH, YOU WERE AWESOME.
>> HERE'S RALPH, HE'S LIKE THIS.
>> WHEN WE COME BACK TO CAMP, I
SEEN RUSSELL WITH A LITTLE
ROLLED UP PIECE OF PAPER,
AND I SAID TO MYSELF, HE HAS GOT
THE DAGGONE CLUE OUT OF THAT
DAGGONE BASKET, SO, RUSSELL HE'S
GOING TO PAY THE PRICE BECAUSE
THIS IS NOT RUSSELL'S GAME.
THIS IS MY GAME.
>> HE'S GOT A CLUE.
>> THE CLUE'S IN THE BASKET.
IT'S ALL OF OURS.
>> FROM NOW ON,
WE TAKE THE REWARD.
>> EXACTLY.
>> WE WERE DOG PADDLING
AT ONE POINT.
AND EVERYBODY WANTS
TO THROW THE BATON.
>> SHE'S LIKE, "I'M GREAT
SWIMMING SHORT DISTANCE."
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU SUCK AT LIFE, OKAY.
>> FROM THE FISHING BASKET RIGHT
NOW, YOU SAW HIM TAKE IT OUT?
>> OF COURSE HE DID,
OF COURSE HE DID.
AFTER OUR VICTORY, SARITA CAME
AND TOLD ME IN THE FISHING GEAR
WE GOT WAS A CLUE,
RUSSELL STUFFED IT
IN HIS POCKET.
RALPH SAW IT.
THAT'S WHAT COMES FROM
EXPERIENCE.
HE KNEW THE CLUE WAS IN THERE.
>> LADIES, I'LL GIVE YOU
THE HONOR.
>> THE GUY IS THE MOST
UNTRUSTWORTHY CHARACTER I'VE
EVER MET IN MY LIFE.
HE PREACHED OVER AND OVER THAT
THIS GAME WAS ABOUT TRUST AND
WHO YOU COULD GO DEEP WITH.
IF WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER SHOW
ME SOME FAITH
AND SHARE THE CLUE.
>> CLUE TO HIDDEN IMMUNITY.
IF THE LOOMING VOTE HAS YOU IN A
SCARY SPOT, THEN I'D LOOK WHERE
SOMETHING IS ALIVE NEXT TO
SOMETHING THAT'S NOT.
>> OKAY.
>> SOMETHING'S DEAD.
>> SOMETHING THAT'S ALIVE,
SOMETHING THAT IS NOT.
I KNEW THEY WERE GOING TO BE
LIKE THIS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, SOMEBODY
DOESN'T HAVE THIS CLUE, IT'S
GOING TO BE HARD
TO SOLVE THE PUZZLE.
>> OBVIOUSLY.
>> OKAY.
>> I HAVE THREE PEOPLE,
THREE VOTES.
THAT'S ALL I NEED.
I NEVER HAD NUMBERS.
I ALWAYS MAKE IT TO THE END.
I DON'T NEED NO STINKIN NUMBERS.
ALL I NEED IS TRUST, LOYALTY.
THAT'S HOW I PLAY THIS GAME.
>> THIS GAME'S GONNA GET
VERY INTERESTING.
>> FOR SURE.
>> SARITA LOOKED TERRIBLE.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> SARITA--
>> YEAH.
>> SHE WAS DOG PADDLING.
>> SHE'S WEAK, SHE'S WEAK.
>> SHE WAS DOG PADDLING
AT ONE POINT.
>> I AGREE.
>> IT WAS A PITIFUL PERFORMANCE.
>> YEAH, WE DIDN'T DO THAT WELL.
>> I MEAN, WE'RE ALL
PLAYERS HERE.
>> FOUR MORE TO WIN.
AND I SAY WE WIN THEM ALL.
>> RUSSELL, THERE WASN'T NO
HIDDEN IMMUNITY CLUE
IN THAT BAG, WAS THERE?
>> MAYBE THERE WAS.
>> I SAW YOU TAKE SOMETHING OUT.
WAS THAT IT?
>> WE WON IT.
YOU DIDN'T WIN IT.
WE ALL WON IT.
>> THERE WASN'T NO CLUE
IN THERE.
>> RUSSELL.
>> CALM DOWN, GUYS.
THIS IS HOW THE GAME'S PLAYED.
YOU EITHER WITH ME
OR AGAINST ME.
>> WE JUST WANT TO KNOW IF THERE
WAS ONE IN THERE.
>> WHAT IF THERE WAS?
>> NO I AIN'T THREATENING YOU.
THOUGH IT WILL BE ALL OF OURS.
>> THAT'S NOT HOW THIS GAME
IS PLAYED, MY FRIEND.
>> WE COULD HAVE EASILY LOST,
RUSSELL AND THEN WHERE IN THE
HELL WOULD YOU HAVE BEEN.
>> YOU DON'T GOT IT?
>> I DON'T HAVE IT.
>> YOU SAY YOU AIN'T GOT IT.
>> I AIN'T GOT IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, BIG BOY.
>> BUT I DON'T LIKE HOW YOU
COMING AT ME.
>> I WAS JUST ASKING YOU.
>> I'M JUST SAYING I DON'T LIKE
HOW YOU COMING AT ME.
>> OH, YOU DON'T?
>> NO.
>> I'M JUST ASKING YOU.
>> I'M JUST LETTING YOU
KNOW THAT.
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
>> I KNOW HOW TO PLAY THIS GAME.
ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME HOW
TO PLAY THE GAME?
>> THIS OLE BOY HERE DOES, TOO.
>> SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> I JUST WANT TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
YOU CAN'T BE HONEST BACK.
THANK YOU, RUSSELL.
HE'S GOT IT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'VE ALREADY GOT ONE.
I DIDN'T NEED IT.
I'LL PLAY HIS GAME.
I'LL SHOW HIM HOW SMART
I CAN BE.
RIGHT ON.
>> WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
RALPH WENT OFF.
HE SAID HE KNOWS HOW
TO PLAY THIS GAME.
HE'S LIKE, "I KNOW HOW
TO PLAY THIS GAME, TOO."
REALLY? REALLY?
YOU JUST DONE THAT TO ME, TO
RUSSELL HANTZ, AND YOU KNOW HOW
TO PLAY THIS GAME?
>> I GOT MY LUXURY ITEM TODAY
IN TREE MAIL.
IT'S A JOURNAL.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN THE NEXT
PERSON COMES
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE DUEL
IS GOING TO ENTAIL.
>> AND I HOPE WE DON'T HAVE
TO COEXIST HERE FOR A WHILE.
THAT WOULD SUCK, ESPECIALLY IF
THAT PERSON WAS PHILLIP.
>> I'D LIKE TO SPEAK FOR A
SECOND LIKE WE DID
AFTER THE LAST CHALLENGE.
I'LL BE VERY BRIEF.
COULD YOU COME OVER
FOR A SECOND, MATT?
THANKS.
>> SO WE GET BACK FROM THE
CHALLENGE, AND ONCE AGAIN, WE
HAVE TO ENDURE THE PRETRIBAL
COUNCIL BEFORE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> I WANT TO SAY TO ALL MY
FELLOW CONTESTANTS
AND TRIBE MEMBERS.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS PERFORMED
GALLANTRY.
YOU WERE OUTSTANDING.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD
OF YOUR EFFORT.
I ONLY WISH I COULD HAVE
PERFORMED IN MY MOMENT AS WELL
AS ALL OF YOU DID TODAY.
AND HAVING SAID THAT, I WANT YOU
TO KNOW I WON'T BE RUNNING
AROUND SAYING, "WILL YOU DO
THIS, WILL YOU DO THAT?"
THE NEXT THING THAT WENT ON
A FEW DAYS AGO.
IT'S NOT NECESSARY.
I'LL LEAVE IT TO THE TRIBE TO
DECIDE WHAT'S BEST
FOR THE TRIBE.
THANK YOU.
IF Y'ALL WANT TO SAY ANYTHING,
FEEL FREE.
OKAY.
>> PHILLIP, PHILLIP.
YOU DID GOOD.
IT'S A TEAM EFFORT.
WE WIN AS A TEAM.
WE LOSE AS A TEAM.
IT SUCKS THAT WE HAVE TO DO WHAT
WE HAVE TO DO NOW, BUT THAT'S
PART OF THE GAME.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> IT COULD HAVE BEEN ANY OF US.
>> COOL, LET'S GET TO WORK.
LET'S GET THIS PLACE READY.
>> LET'S GET THAT FIRE GOING.
>> PHILLIP BLEW THE CHALLENGE,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
BUT LOOK, WE JUST GOT OUR ASSES
WHIPPED TWICE, AND MATT GOES TO
CONGRATULATE THE OTHER TEAM.
MATT'S TRYING TO PLAY THE GOOD
CHRISTIAN GAME AND THE SOCIAL
GAME AND THE END GAME ON DAY
FRIGGIN' FIVE.
WAKE UP, BROTHER.
>> PHIL.
ARE YOU WORRIED?
>> THAT LOOKS PRETTY ON YOU.
>> OH, THANKS.
>> NO.
BECAUSE I'M A STRONG MAN.
AND IF IT'S TO BE REDEMPTION,
I KIND OF LIKE THAT NAME.
>> TONIGHT I'M PLAYING THE IDOL.
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
THEY STILL HAVE ENOUGH VOTES
TO VOTE OFF WHOEVER THEY WANT.
SO THEY'RE NO WAY THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO TAKE THE CHANCE AND LET
ME SLIP BAY AGAIN SO I'M PLAYING
IT FOR SURE,
WHICH IS REALLY SAD.
>> SO WHAT ARE WE DOING?
>> I DON'T KNOW, DO YOU TRUST
MATT AND ANDREA THAT THEY'LL
STAY WITH US?
>> ANDREA IS DECENT
IN CHALLENGES.
LIKE, SHE'S A STRENGTH,
I FEEL LIKE.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, MAN--
>> I UNDERSTAND WE--
>> WE'RE IN A WEIRD SPOT.
IT'S LIKE WHAT DO WE DO,
GET RID OF MATT.
IT'S CRAZY. IT'S CRAZY.
BUT THIS IS SUCH A WEIRD SPOT
WE'RE IN RIGHT NOW.
THEY'LL NEVER EXPECT FOUR OF US
TO VOTE FOR MATT.
I DON'T WANT TO VOTE FOR MATT,
BUT, HONESTLY, HIM GOING OVER TO
THE OTHER TRIBE,
IT MAKES ME SICK.
>> I KNOW, IT'S NOT COOL.
>> IT MAKES ME SICK.
>> IT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO SEE
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE HEAT OF THE
MOMENT OF A CHALLENGE YOU LOST
YOUR TEAMMATE GOING OVER
AND SHAKING HANDS.
I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S A TIME AND PLACE FOR
THOSE THINGS, AND THAT
WASN'T ONE OF THOSE TIMES.
WE JUST ALL FOUR FOR MATT?
>> FOUR OF US VOTE FOR MATT
AND THAT'S IT.
BUT WE TELL MATT AND ANDREA
WE'RE SPLITTING VOTES.
AND THEN WE'LL FIND OUT IF THEY
WERE FIGURING TO SCREW US.
WE'LL SEE WHEN THE VOTES
COME THROUGH.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW?
I DON'T REALLY WANT TO VOTE
MATT OUT.
I LIKE HIM, BUT, HEY,
IT HAPPENS.
>> THE FIRST GAME PLAN WAS TO
VOTE OUT PHILLIP OR ANDREA.
WELL, MATT'S GETTING FOUR VOTES.
I DIDN'T WANT TO PLAY "SURVIVOR"
LIKE THIS.
I REALLY DIDN'T.
I WANTED TO KEEP MY TEAM STRONG.
I MEAN, I GET IT.
MATT'S PLAYING "SURVIVOR."
HE'S PLAYING TEXTBOOK.
BUT HE'S PLAYING WITH ME.
>> ALL OF US ARE SAFE AND
THERE'S NO WAY ANY OF US
GO HOME.
SO HOW DO WE WANT TO DO IT?
>> LET'S JUST SPLIT IT.
>> KEEP IT SIMPLE.
GIRLS KRISTINA.
GUYS PHIL.
>> THE PLAN IS WE ARE GOING
TO SPLIT THE VOTES.
GIRLS VOTE FOR KRISTINA, GUYS
VOTE FOR PHILLIP AND WE'RE
ASSUMING KRISTINA WILL USE THE
IDOL AND PHILLIP WILL GO HOME.
>> DONE?
DONE.
>> AS FAR AS MATT AND ANDREA
ARE CONCERNED WE'RE GOING TO
SPLIT VOTES 3-3.
THE GIRLS ARE ALL VOTING
FOR CHRISTINE.
THE GUYS ARE ALL
VOTING FOR PHILLIP.
BUT IN ALL ACTUALITY,
NONE OF THAT IS HAPPENING.
MYSELF, ASHLEY, NATALIE, AND
GRANT, WE'RE ALL VOTING
FOR MATT.
AND CHRISTINE WITH THIS IDOL,
SHE BETTER PLAY THAT THING.
IF SHE PLAYS THE IDOL WE CAN
BREAK UP ANDREA AND MATT,
IT'S A HOME RUN.
>> COULD YOU TELL ME WHO DO YOU
WANT ME TO VOTE FOR?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WE'LL SEE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU LET ME KNOW.
>> HE DOESN'T HAVE
A SINGLE PLAY.
HE HAS NOWHERE TO GO.
>> HE WANTS ME TO TELL HIM WHAT
TO DO AND SPARE HIM, BUT--
>> BUT IT WOULDN'T BE
SPARING HIM.
>> NO.
>> HEY, MAN, LET'S TAKE A WALK.
>> EVERY DAY ROB IMPRESSES ME.
LIKE, IT IS UNBELIEVABLE HOW
WELL HE CAN JUST TALK TO PEOPLE
AND PLAY THIS GAME AND SEE WHAT
THEY NEED AND FULFILL THAT NEED.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY AMAZING.
>> SO THE WHEELS ARE IN MOTION
FOR EVERYTHING TO HAPPEN.
AND EVERYTHING'S GONNA HAPPEN
THE WAY IT SHOULD HAPPEN.
I STILL DON'T KNOW WHO IT'S
GOING TO BE YET.
WE HAVEN'T DECIDED,
BUT NO MATTER WHO IT IS,
I'M TELLING YOU,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
>> OKAY I'LL TAKE YOU
ON YOUR WORD, MAN.
>> HERE'S THE THING.
YOU HAVE TO-- LIKE, FIRST OF
ALL, DON'T GO OFF ON A TIRADE AT
TRIBAL LIKE DID YOU LAST TIME.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO PULL ONE
OVER ON YOU.
I HAVE NO REASON TO.
PHILLIP'S A TOUGH COOKIE.
I LITERALLY HAVE TO WAIT UNTIL
ONE MINUTE BEFORE WE GO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I MAY ACTUALLY EVEN HAVE TO TELL
HIM AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHO TO VOTE FOR BECAUSE PHILLIP
LIKES TO TALK A LOT.
HE'S LIABLE TO RUN AROUND AND
TELL EVERYBODY IN THE GROUP
EVERYTHING WE'RE DOING.
THE PLAN IS BIGGER
THAN JUST TONIGHT.
SO HERE'S THE DEAL.
WHEN THE TIME COMES TO VOTE, I'M
GONNA TAKE MY RIGHT HAND AND PUT
IT ON THE SHOULDER OF THE PERSON
I WANT YOU TO VOTE FOR.
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> BUT YOU NEED TO FEEL
LIKE YOU'RE GOING HOME.
>> OKAY.
>> OBVIOUSLY, THE WAY THINGS
ARE GOING, YOU KNOW, THE WAY--
IN ORDER FOR EVERYTHING TO WORK
OUT-- YOU'RE A SMART GUY.
YOU CAN FIGURE OUT WHERE
WE'RE GOING WITH ALL OF THIS.
>> RIGHT.
>> KIND OF LIKE--
YOU'RE AN ACTOR, BRO.
I KNOW IT MAY BE ME TONIGHT,
AND IF IT IS--
>> OKAY.
YOU WANT ME TO SAY THAT NOW?
>> NOT RIGHT NOW.
A LITTLE LATER.
THIS WILL BE A GOOD TEST TO SEE
IF PHILLIP DOES WHAT HE SAYS
HE'S GOING TO DO.
AND IF HE DOES, HE CAN START TO
EARN HIS WAY BACK
INTO THE ROTATION.
IF I GET THERE TONIGHT, AND
PHILLIP STARTS TELLING EVERYBODY
WHAT I TOLD HIM,
PHILLIP WILL BE SENT PACKING.
>> Jeff: KRISTINA, AT THE LAST
TRIBAL, A LOT OF ATTENTION
FOCUSED ON YOU.
YOU CHOSE NOT TO PLAY THE IDOL,
WHICH YOU ARE NOW WEARING
AROUND YOUR NECK.
EVEN THOUGH EVERYBODY KNEW YOU
HAD IT, AND YOU WERE ON
THE HOT SEAT A LITTLE BIT.
>> WELL, I JUST HAD A FEELING
THAT I SHOULDN'T PLAY IT, THAT I
WASN'T GOING TO GET
ALL THE VOTES.
IT WAS A REALLY TOUGH DECISION,
THOUGH.
>> Jeff: DO YOU HAVE A FEELING
TONIGHT AS TO WHETHER OR NOT
YOU'RE GOING TO PLAY IT?
>> JUST A LITTLE ONE.
JUST A LITTLE ONE.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, I ASKED YOU
BEFORE THE CHALLENGE, DOES THIS
BRING OUT THE ANIMAL IN YOU?
AND YOU SAID ABSOLUTELY.
>> THE GORILLA.
A POWERFUL ANIMAL.
WON'T ATTACK UNLESS PROVOKED.
THE LION, ONE OF THE FEW
ANIMALS THAT NO ANIMAL,
WHETHER STARVING TO DEATH,
WILL APPROACH.
FOR ME, THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT
MY FAMILY AND MY COUNTRY.
YOU DO SOMETHING
TO THE UNITED STATES,
THAT FULL POWER
IS GOING TO COME AT YOU.
YOU TRY TO ATTACK MY FAMILY IN
ANY WAY, YOU GET THE LION, BABY.
>> Jeff: NOW, WHAT DOES THE
LION OR THE GORILLA DO TO ITSELF
IF IT FEELS IT SCREWED UP?
>> I DON'T THINK A LION EVER
FEELS LIKE IT SCREWS UP,
BECAUSE IT KIND OF DELIVERS.
AND A GORILLA THEY EITHER GET
BEAT DOWN BY ANOTHER SILVERBACK,
BECAUSE IT'S SURVIVOR OF THE
FITTEST, OR THEY DON'T LOSE,
AND I LOST.
AND I NEED TO SUFFER THE
CONSEQUENCES OF THAT LOSS.
>> Jeff: BOSTON ROB, WHAT DO
YOU SAY TO PHILLIP WHEN HE SAYS,
"LOOK, IT'S ALL ME."
THERE'S A WHOLE GROUP HERE.
>> I THINK PHILLIP
IS A COMPETITOR.
HE TAKES IT VERY PERSONAL
AND VERY HARD.
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT BECAUSE
I'M A COMPETITOR, TOO.
AND I SAID, "LOOK, WE WIN
AS A TEAM.
WE LOSE AS A TEAM."
BUT I UNDERSTAND HOW HE FEELS.
I'D INTERNALIZE IT AND I'D FEEL
LIKE IT WAS MY FAULT, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO, MATT, YOU HAVE
SOMEBODY NOW SAYING VOTE ME OUT.
I DESERVE IT.
I LOST THIS CHALLENGE.
ON THE FLIP SIDE, HE'S ONE OF
YOUR BIGGEST GUYS.
>> I MEAN, HE'S A HUGE ASSET,
EVEN AROUND CAMP.
I MEAN, IT'S TOUGH TO CONSIDER
VOTING SOMEONE OUT
FOR A SINGLE MISTAKE.
BUT IN THIS GAME, IT CAN HAPPEN
AS QUICKLY AS THAT, AND SO I'M
JUST REALLY NOT SURE
AT THIS POINT.
THERE'S A LOT OF UNCERTAINTY
WITH THIS VOTE FOR SOME REASON.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, TO WORK SO
HARD TO GET HERE, IT CAN'T BE
EASY TO BE ON THE VERGE
OF WALKING OUT OF HERE.
>> WHEN I GET TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND, I'M NOT GOING TO LAY
DOWN AND DIE BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY
TO MEET MY NEMESIS.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jeff: FRAN-CHES-QWA.
>> NOTHING LIKE
A LITTLE PAYBACK.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE LOOKING
FORWARD IF VOTED OUT TONIGHT
GOING TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> I WOULD HAVE LOVE TO HAVE
STAYED BUT THERE IS SOME UPSIDE.
>> Jeff: MATT, ARE PEOPLE
SPENDING MUCH TIME TALKING ABOUT
REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHAT IT MIGHT
BE LIKE, WHAT THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO ENDURE?
>> THE TWO MAIN QUESTIONS
IT'S KIND OF FOCUSED AROUND
ARE HOW MANY PEOPLE
COME BACK FROM
REDEMPTION ISLAND
AND AT WHAT TIME?
>> Jeff: IT WOULD BE GREAT
IF YOU KNEW THAT.
>> I MEAN, IF WE KNEW THAT,
IT WOULD BE A HUGE ADVANTAGE.
I MEAN, THIS RAIN IS COMING
SIDEWAYS RIGHT NOW, AND WE DON'T
WANT ANYBODY OUT THERE BY
THEMSELVES, WE REALLY DON'T.
BUT THAT'S JUST "SURVIVOR"
I SUPPOSE.
>> Jeff: IT IS ONE OF THE
UNIQUE TWISTS OF THIS SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR," AND ONE OF YOU IS
ABOUT TO JOIN FRANCESCA ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ANDREA, YOU'RE UP.
>> KRISTINA, FOR LYING AND BEING
A MANIPULATOR, ALONG WITH YOUR
FRIEND, FRANCESCA.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I HOPE YOU DON'T HOLD IT
AGAINST ME, BUD,
AND WE'LL SEE YOU
ON THE FLIP SIDE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN--
>> JEFF.
I THINK I'M GOING TO NEED
A LITTLE EXTRA HELP TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST KRISTINA
TONIGHT WILL NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KRISTINA.
DOES NOT COUNT.
KRISTINA.
PHILLIP.
ONE VOTE PHILLIP.
PHIL.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP.
MATT.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP,
ONE VOTE MATT.
MATT.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP,
TWO VOTES MATT.
MATT.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: THAT'S THREE VOTES
MATT, TWO VOTES PHILLIP,
ONE VOTE LEFT.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,"
MATT.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD WORK, GUYS.
MY GOODNESS.
>> Jeff: MATT, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A SECOND SHOT
TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> HAVE FUN.
>> DAMN, GUYS.
>> Jeff: ONLY YOUR SECOND
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND ALREADY A
VICIOUS BLINDSIDE.
YOU GUYS ARE LEARNING
THIS GAME QUICKLY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> I'M STILL REALLY PISSED
ABOUT WHAT THEY DID.
>> Jeff: ROB FINDS OUT HELL
HATH HAS NO FURY
LIKE ANDREA SCORNED.
>> SHE'LL CUT MY THROAT.
>> Jeff: AND THE ZAPATERA TRIBE
FINDS OUT WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU CROSS RUSSELL.
>> I'M DEALING WITH A BUNCH
OF BITCHES.
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE
THE BIGGEST BLINDSIDE EVER.
>> I'VE BEEN ON AN EMOTIONAL
ROLLER COASTER.
SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE
I JUST WANT TO GO HOME.
AND THERE ARE OTHER TIMES I
THINK ROB JUST SET ME UP TO HAVE
THE GREATEST COMEBACK
IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
>> I'M SHOCKED.
>> I JUST HAVE TO STAY STRONG
AND THE LORD WILL BE WITH ME.