>> Jeff: WE'RE ON BOARD A
HELICOPTER PILOTED BY THE
NICARAGUAN AIR FORCE, FLYING
OVER THE PACIFIC OCEAN IN
CENTRAL AMERICA, WHERE THESE
AMERICANS HAVE ALREADY BEGUN THE
ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME.
EACH CASTAWAY IS ARRIVING WITH
NOTHING BUT THE CLOTHES ON THEIR
BACK AND THEIR OWN UNIQUE STORY.
>> I'M THE C.E.O. OF MY OWN
SOFTWARE COMPANY.
BUT ARE THERE OTHER LAYERS
ON ME? ABSOLUTELY.
I'M A FORMER FEDERAL AGENT.
THAT'S RIGHT,
SPECIAL AGENT SHEPPARD.
THAT WAS MY FIRST
AND MIDDLE NAME FOR YEARS.
>> MY FAITH IS EVERYTHING.
MY ENTIRE LIFE REVOLVES
AROUND IT.
I PRAY EVERY DAY AS I STRIVE TO
BECOME MORE LIKE MY SAVIOR.
>> THEY WILL CALL ME A REDNECK,
ONE CRAZY, STUDENT BASTARD.
WE AIN'T EVER HAD A DUMB ASS
WIN THE GAME, HAVE WE?
>> Jeff: IT'S THE ULTIMATE
CHALLENGE, A GROUP OF STRANGERS
FORCED TO WORK TOGETHER WHILE
BATTLING THE ELEMENTS
AND EACH OTHER.
THEY MUST LEARN TO ADAPT OR
THEY'LL BE VOTED OUT.
IN THE END, ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
TO CLAIM THE MILLION-DOLLAR
PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 18 PEOPLE,
ONE SURVIVOR.
♪ ♪
>> Jeff: COME ON, LET'S GO.
EVERYBODY OFF!
>> WE'RE ON THE BEACH, AND WE
SAW THE MATS AND IT'S LIKE,
OH, WOW.
THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING.
I'M REALLY ON "SURVIVOR."
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
LET'S HEAD IN.
>> I WAS IN THE MARINE CORPS.
SPENT TWO DEPLOYMENTS,
WENT TO IRAQ TWICE.
I THINK I'M GOING TO WIN JUST
BECAUSE OF MY BACKGROUND.
I THINK I'VE BEEN TRAINED FOR
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: BEFORE WE GET
STARTED, WE'VE GOT TWO MORE
PLAYERS JOINING US.
RIGHT HERE.
>> IS THAT ROB?
>> BOSTON ROB!
( CHEERS )
>> OH, NO.
>> NO.
>> OH, NO!
>> OH, MY GOD!
IT'S RUSSELL.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHOSE TEAM
HE'S GOING TO BE ON, BUT I'M
GOING TO STARE DOWN RUSSELL, AND
I KNOW WHEN I STARE DOWN
RUSSELL, HE'LL KNOW, OH, SHE'S
GOT A LITTLE EVIL INSIDE OF HER
BECAUSE IF I'M NOT THE ONE
PERSON HE PICKS TO KEEP TO THE
END, THEN NO MATTER WHAT, I'M
GOING TO BE OUT.
I'M GONNA BE OUT.
>> Jeff: I THINK EVERYBODY
HERE IS FAMILIAR WITH BOSTON ROB
AND RUSSELL.
BOSTON ROB HAS PROVEN HIS
ABILITY TO HELP A TRIBE NOT ONLY
IN CHALLENGES, BUT IN CAMP LIFE.
HE HAS PLAYED THREE TIMES.
HE'S MADE IT TO THE FINAL ONCE.
HE HAS NEVER WON.
RUSSELL, IN BACK-TO-BACK
SEASONS, RUSSELL MASTERMINDED
TWO OF THE STRONGEST ALLIANCES
IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
RUSSELL HAS PLAYED TWICE.
HE'S BEEN TO THE END TWICE.
HE HAS NEVER WON.
TOGETHER, THESE TWO OFFER 156
DAYS OF "SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE.
THAT IS WORTH A TON OUT HERE.
>> THEY'RE SIZING US UP LIKE
WE'RE PREY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> FRANCESCA.
>> Jeff: FRANCESCA,
WHAT'S YOUR REACTION?
YOU SAID THESE GUYS WERE SIZING
YOU UP AS PREY?
>> YEAH, THEY'RE TROUBLE MAKERS.
THEY'RE TWO OF THE MOST FAMOUS
TROUBLE MAKERS IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY SO I DON'T THINK THEY'RE
HERE JUST TO HELP US OUT.
>> Jeff: SO THE QUESTION NOW
IS WHO IS GOING TO WHICH TRIBE?
WE'RE GOING TO DO IT OLD SCHOOL,
GUYS.
WE'RE GOING TO DRAW FOR BUFFS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: THEY'RE COVERED, SO
WE'RE NOT GIVING ANYTHING AWAY.
ROB, TAKE YOUR PICK.
RUSSELL, THIS IS FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S REVEAL.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> YES!
>> Jeff: ROB.
YOU JOIN OMETEPE.
TAKE A SPOT.
>> ALL RIGHT, BABY!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL HANTZ, YOU
JOIN ZAPATERA.
>> COME ON, RUSSELL!
LET'S GO, BUDDY.
>> WE WELCOME YOU.
>> Jeff: TAKE A SPOT.
( APPLAUSE )
>> JOIN IN!
JOIN IN!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THERE IS
ONE MORE TWIST.
WHEN YOU ARE VOTED OUT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, YOU WILL NOT GO HOME.
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: INSTEAD, YOU WILL
LEAVE TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND YOU
WILL BE SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WHERE YOU WILL LIVE ALONE.
YOU WILL HAVE THE SAME BASIC
SUPPLIES THAT YOUR TRIBEMATES
HAD BACK AT CAMP, BUT IT WILL BE
UP TO YOU TO KEEP
THE SHELTER GOING.
IT WILL BE UP TO YOU
TO TEND THE FIRE.
TO FEED YOURSELF.
IT WILL NOT BE EASY.
WHEN THE NEXT PERSON JOINS YOU
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND, THE TWO OF
YOU WILL SQUARE OFF IN A DUEL.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: THE WINNER STAYS.
THE LOSER IS OUT OF THE GAME
FOR GOOD.
AT A CERTAIN POINT IN THE GAME,
THE REMAINING PERSON ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND WILL BE
ALLOWED TO RE-ENTER THE GAME AND
CONTINUE THEIR PURSUIT OF THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR, AND THE
MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
>> SWEET!
>> REDEMPTION ISLAND DOES NOT
SCARE ME ONE BIT.
IT'S A VACATION.
YEAH.
PUT ME ON THAT ISLAND,
SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO WIN THE
CHALLENGE AND I'M GOING TO COME
BACK AND I'M GOING TO TAKE SOME
HEADS OFF.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
STARTED WITH THIS GAME?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE,
A MAP TO YOUR CAMP.
ZAPATERA, A MAP TO YOUR CAMP.
IT IS GOING TO RAIN A LOT OUT
HERE IN NICARAGUA.
I SUGGEST YOU GET TO CAMP
QUICKLY, START USING THE
EXPERIENCE OF ROB AND RUSSELL,
START BUILDING CAMP.
OMETEPE, YOU'RE HEADING OUT
THAT WAY.
ZAPATERA, THAT WAY.
>> WHEN JEFF TOLD US WHAT
REDEMPTION ISLAND IS, I WAS
LIKE, I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO
PROCESS IT.
I MEAN, IT MAKES ROB AND RUSSELL
BEING HERE A LOT MORE
COMPLICATED BECAUSE THEY COULD
DEFINITELY COME BACK INTO THE
GAME EVEN IF WE GET RID OF THEM.
THE GOOD PART OF IT IS THAT IF I
GET VOTED OUT, I COULD COME BACK
INTO THE GAME.
BUT THE POSSIBILITY OF GETTING
VOTED OUT WAS SO NOT A REALITY
TO ME THAT I ONLY SAW IT AS A
DOWNSIDE.
I'M LIKE, DAMN IT!
SOMEONE I VOTE OUT IS GOING TO
COME BACK TO HAUNT ME.
CRAP.
>> AS SOON AS I WALKED TO THE
CAMP, I WAS SO GREATFUL TO BE
BACK TO GET MY TITLE
OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> THE POWER OF PURPLE.
>> THE FIRST TWO,
I WAS A SCHOOL BOY.
THIS ONE, I'M BRINGING IT.
>> STEVE.
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE
THE NEW ME.
I'M GOING TO BE THE LEADER
TO MY TRIBE.
WHEN I SIT THEM ALL DOWN AND I
TAKE CONTROL OF THE CAMP, I'LL
BECOME THE LEADER OF THE CAMP.
>> ATTENTION.
EVERYBODY, ATTENTION.
>> I GOT A LITTLE SOMETHING
TO SAY.
YOU KNOW, YOU SEE IT ON TV, IT
SEEMS EASY.
I PROMISE YOU, YOU'RE ABOUT TO
EXPERIENCE THE TOUGHEST THING
THAT YOU'VE EVER BEEN THROUGH IN
YOUR ENTIRE LIFE.
I'M NOT HERE TO SABOTAGE
ANYTHING FROM NOBODY.
IF I CAME BACK AND DID SOMETHING
LIKE THAT, IT WOULD BE PRETTY
STUPID OF ME.
I'M HERE TO WIN.
>> RIGHT ON.
>> LET'S DO IT!
>> GOOD JOB ZAPATERA.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
ZAPATERA!
>> I THINK ANYBODY WHO DOESN'T
THINK RUSSELL IS DANGEROUS
IS FOOLISH.
HE'S PLAYED THE GAME TWICE AND
ENDED UP IN THE FINALS TWICE.
HE HASN'T WON AND THERE'S NO
MYSTERY WHY HE HASN'T WON.
IT'S THE WAY HE'S CHOSEN TO PLAY
THE GAME BOTH TIMES.
HE'S TOO AGGRESSIVE AND HE WANTS
THE BLOOD ON HIS HANDS.
>> ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
LET'S TAKE IT AWAY.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> OKAY.
>> WHEN I SEEN A BIG BOX OF
NAILS AND ALL THAT, I LOVE IT.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT.
WE'VE GOT IT ALL.
>> CAN'T WAIT TO GET STARTED.
I'VE CAMPED.
I'VE BUILT CABINS.
I'VE DONE ALL THIS KIND
OF STUFF.
WE CAN PUT IT RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT HERE'S ANOTHER FORK.
WE DONE GOT OUR SLOPE.
THEY LISTEN TO ME, I BELIEVE WE
CAN BUILD A DECENT SHACK.
SOME OF THEM I DON'T THINK KNOWS
WHAT'S GOING ON BUT I DON'T WANT
THEM TO KNOW THAT.
>> SUPERHERO NICKNAME,
STEEL WOOL.
YOU CAN GET THROUGH ANYTHING
WITH A LITTLE BIT
OF ELBOW GREASE.
AND YOU HAVE THE MOST IMPRESSIVE
MAN SWEATER I HAVE EVER SEEN.
FIRST IMPRESSION,
VERY GOOD IMPRESSION.
I THINK WE HAVE A BUNCH
OF WORKER BEES WHICH IS GOOD.
AS LONG AS WE CAN WIN AND STAY
AWAY FROM THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES, I THINK WE'RE GOING
TO DO DAMN WELL.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> GET UP THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT!
PUT IT IN THERE.
OKAY.
>> OKAY, RALPH,
TELL US WHAT YOU NEED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> CAN YOU GRAB A NAIL.
>> HEAL, YEAH.
>> READY TO WATCH
THE FIRST INJURY.
>> HELP HIM. HELP HIM.
>> THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO.
>> WELL DONE.
>> DID IT HIT RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE?
>> I THINK SO.
>> OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
>> THIS IS A STUPID QUESTION--
YOU ARE FROM BOSTON, AREN'T YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> THINGS ARE GOING REALLY WELL
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S JUST SUCH A BLESSING
TO HAVE ROB HERE.
WITH HIS HISTORY IN CONSTRUCTION
AND HIS HAVING BEEN HERE AND HIS
LAID BACK APPROACH IS REALLY
BRINGING A LOT OF HARMONY
TO THIS TRIBE.
WE MIGHT AS WELL CALL IT
CAMP HARMONY RIGHT NOW.
>> JUST STOP US AND TELL US--
>> YOU'RE THE PRO HERE.
>> YOU GUYS KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
>> I AM SO GLAD THAT WE HAVE
BOSTON ROB.
HE'S AMAZING.
I'M JUST HAVING SO MUCH FUN
WITH HIM.
AND I FEEL LIKE A SENSE OF
COMFORT AND I THINK IF RUSSELL
WAS HERE, WE WOULD ALL BE ON
EDGE, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE HE'S NUTS.
YOU KNOW, HE WOULD HAVE-- OH,
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN CRAZY.
>> HEY, GUYS.
LISTEN.
BECAUSE OF THE SIZE OF THESE
BEAMS, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE THE
OPENING BE THAT WAY, WE WERE
SAYING, BECAUSE THAT'S THE WATER
RUN-DOWN, AND WE GET THIS WHOLE
BANK HERE PROTECTING US
FROM THE WIND.
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME DO THAT?
>> I DON'T MIND DIGGING.
>> NO, NO, IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
IT'S THE WAY YOU'RE DOING IT.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT, PUT
THE WEIGHT LIKE THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT,
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
I MEAN, PROBABLY THE MOST
ANNOYING PERSON SO FAR
IS PHILLIP.
>> DO YOU WANT TO HELP DIG?
>> YEAH, DO YOU NEED HELP?
>> SURE, THERE ARE GOING TO BE
TWO MORE HOLES OVER THERE.
I'LL JUST FINISH UP HERE.
>> I MEAN, HE'S JUST GOT THAT
AGGRESSIVE KIND OF LIKE, IN YOUR
FACE PERSONALITY, WHICH, YOU
KNOW, YOU JUST NEED TO BE
CAREFUL OUT HERE BECAUSE THAT'S
THE KIND OF THING THAT CAN JUST
TURN PEOPLE OFF.
>> WHEN YOU HAMMER, IF YOU
STRIKE THIS WAY-- LIKE, IF YOU
MISS THIS IT CAN GO LIKE THAT
AND HIT YOU.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO HAMMER THIS
WAY, PUT THIS FOOT OUT.
I'M WITH YOU.
>> APPARENTLY, MY HATCHETING
ISN'T THE CORRECT TECHNIQUE, BUT
I MEAN, I DON'T EVEN HAVE THE
BEST AIM, SO I'M JUST
GOING AT IT.
I GREW UP ON A FARM SO I KNOW
HOW TO USE AN AXE
AND I KNOW HOW TO HAMMER.
I THINK HE JUST LIKES PLAYING
THE FATHER ROLE A LITTLE BIT,
SO JUST LET HIM DO THAT.
>> I THINK HE LIKES THAT.
>> I KNOW!
>> YOU'RE EXCITED THERE.
>> I WAS JUST THINKING,
IT'S A GOOD PLACE TO BE.
I WANT ALL OF YOU TO COME OVER.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
ABOUT MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, I HAD TO DEBATE
WHETHER OR NOT I WAS GOING TO
TELL YOU, WHETHER OR NOT I WAS
GOING TO REVEAL IT.
I'M A FORMER FEDERAL AGENT.
I DID IT FOR THREE
SEPARATE AGENCIES
SO WHEN I GIVE YOU MY WORD, IF I
SAY SOMETHING, IT'S GOING TO BE
MY WORD.
THE OTHER THING IS I'M AN EXPERT
IN ANALYZING PEOPLE'S BEHAVIOR.
SO I CAN DETERMINE MOST OF THE
TIME WHETHER OR NOT SOMEONE IS
TELLING ME THE TRUTH OR NOT AND
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO BE ABLE
TO DO WHEN WE FINALLY MERGE AND
WE GET TO THE OTHER SIDE.
AND I'LL TELL YOU, IF THAT'S A
FRIEND OR NOT.
OKAY?
AND ALL I WANT TO SAY IS I'VE
GOT SEVEN SISTERS AND I LOVE
WOMEN, OKAY.
( LAUGHTER )
>> YOU MADE THE RIGHT MOVE.
>> ONE OF THE BEST THINGS ABOUT
PHILLIP IS THE COMIC RELIEF
THAT'S PROVIDED BY THE FACT THAT
HE THINKS HE USED TO BE A
FEDERAL AGENT IS, LIKE, THIS BIG
SECRET, LIKE, BOMBSHELL THAT HE
HAS, THAT HE'S HOLDING.
YOU KNOW, IT WILL JUST BLOW
EVERYONE'S MIND IF THEY KNEW.
IT'S HILARIOUS.
WHO CARES?
>> WE HAVE A WHOLE BASKET FULL
OF STUFF, AND NO ONE IS LOOKING
FOR THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL,
THE CLUE TO IT WHICH IS KIND OF
WEIRD BECAUSE DON'T YOU THINK
MAYBE IT'S SOMEWHERE
IN THE STUFF.
>> WHAT IS YOUR FIRST NAME?
>> KRISTINA.
I HAVE GONE THINKING MAYBE YOU
COULD GO THROUGH THIS STUFF HERE
AND CHECK IT OUT AND SEE IF
THERE'S ANYTHING USEFUL
IN IN THERE?
>> I ALREADY DID.
IT'S JUST PIECES OF CLOTH, AND
THERE ARE SCISSORS AND YARN, AND
A SEWING BOX.
>> MAYBE MATT, IF MATT WANTS --
I KNOW YOU KNOW WHAT'S UP.
SO GO THROUGH IT.
>> I WENT THROUGH IT.
>> NOTHING?
>> I'VE GONE THROUGH EVERYTHING
EXCEPT THIS.
I CAN'T OPEN IT.
>> OKAY, I'LL TRY TO KEEP
THEM AWAY.
SEE WHAT YOU CAN FIND.
>> EVERYTHING IS REALLY NEW.
EVERYONE IS TRYING TO GET
THEIR FOOTING.
THE FACT THAT ROB NOTICED I WAS
LOOKING FOR THE CLUE IT WORRIES
ME A LITTLE BIT BECAUSE I DON'T
WANT TO COME OFF AS THIS REALLY
AGGRESSIVE STRATEGIZER
AND TURN PEOPLE OFF.
HOPEFULLY HE'S THE ONLY PERSON
THAT UNDERSTOOD WHAT WAS GOING
ON, BUT IT DRIVES ME CRAZY.
I WANT IT.
>> DUDE, OUR TRIBE, MAN, WE'RE
THE BOMB.
>> OKAY.
>> FIVE GIRLS AND FOUR GUYS.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> YOU KNOW, WHAT I'M SAYING.
SO JUST--
>> I'M REALLY GOOD WITH GIRLS.
>> SO AM I--
>> WE'LL WORK THAT OUT.
>> WE'VE GOT TO KEEP
OUR EYES OPEN.
>> I DEFINITELY WANT TO BE
WORKING TOGETHER.
>> ME, TOO.
>> I'M SERIOUS ABOUT THAT.
>> WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT LATER.
BUT SOMEONE WITH A GOOD WORK
ETHIC AND ON THE SAME PAGE AS ME
>> YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
I HEARD SOMEBODY SAY TO ME,
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THIS GAME A LOT
OF PEOPLE GET REALLY SUPER
PARANOID.
THE THING ABOUT ME
AND ANY SHEPPARD, NO.
I MEAN, ROB IS SIZING ME UP.
SO I LIKE TO THINK OF IT LIKE
TWO MALE LIONS.
( GROWLS )
THEY'RE CHECKING EACH OTHER OUT.
THEY'RE DOING THAT WHOLE THING
AND THEY'RE DOING A LITTLE DANCE
BUT THERE WILL COME A POINT--
OKAY, WHERE THAT'S GOING
TO TAKE OVER.
I THOUGHT THIS WOULD BE
A GOOD TIME
FOR US TO TALK A LITTLE BIT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'M GOING TO NEED YOUR HELP
KEEPING THOSE YOUNG GIRLS FROM
NOT HAVING TOO MUCH.
LOOK AT ME.
ROB ALREADY SAID TO ME YOU GOTTA
WATCH THOSE GIRLS.
THERE ARE MORE GIRLS HERE.
>> THERE ARE.
HE'D BE AN IDIOT NOT TO.
>> HE'S GOING TO TRY TO DIVIDE
AND CONQUER.
HE'S GOING TO TRY TO PLAY ME
LIKE A FOOL.
AND I'M GOING TO PLAY ALONG.
AND I'M GOING TO STICK
TO THE GIRLS.
>> I LIKE YOU, AND DEFINITELY
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT YOU
THAT'S REALLY SOLID.
BUT--
>> I'VE GOT A LITTLE INTEGRITY.
>> I DO, TOO.
>> IN TERMS OF WHAT I TELL
PEOPLE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> AND I THINK YOU AND I CAN
WORK TOGETHER.
AND--
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M TOTALLY ON BOARD.
>> OKAY, COOL.
LET'S GO FIND SOME LOGS,
ALL RIGHT?
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
THIS TRIBE?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF WE'RE ON THE
WINNING SIDE, TO TELL YOU, FROM
THE LOOKS OF IT.
THE OTHER TEAM, I'M TELLING YOU,
THEY LOOK MORE PHYSICAL.
RUSSELL AND I WERE LOOKING FOR
THE TREE MAIL, AND HE CAME UP TO
ME AND I GOT ALL NERVOUS BECAUSE
I FELT LIKE, OH, PROM DATE.
>> WHO DID I BRING
THE FIRST TIME?
WHAT WAS HER NAME.
>> NATALIE.
>> WHO DID I BRING
THE SECOND TIME?
>> PARVE TEE.
>> BUT YOUR SPEECH, RUSSELL,
ABOUT HOW YOU CHANGED.
IT WAS JUST-- IT WAS SO MOVING
TO ME.
IT WAS.
I BELIEVED YOU.
>> LISTEN--
>> I BELIEVED YOU.
YOU ARE A CHANGED MAN.
>> YOU HAVE TO GET
ON THE RIGHT TEAM.
I THINK WE CAN DO
SOMETHING TOGETHER.
BUT THIS IS DANGEROUS BECAUSE
I'M NOT GOING TO BE WALKING
AROUND WITH YOU THAT MUCH
BECAUSE YOU--
YOU-- YOU ARE THAT GIRL.
>> I THINK IT'S BETTER
THAT YOU DON'T.
>> ME AND YOU, WHEN WE GET TO
THE MERGE, IT WILL BE OVER.
>> DONE.
>> THAT'S ALL WE GOTTA DO IS GET
TO THE MERGE.
>> RUSSELL IS SO SNEAKY.
HE WAS LIKE, "LET'S FORM
AN ALLIANCE."
WHICH IS GREAT BECAUSE HE MADE
IT TO THE TOP THREE EVERY TIME
HE PLAYED.
SO, OF COURSE I SAID YES.
>> HE'S GETTING THE GIRLS.
>> PLEASE, GOD,
DON'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
>> WE DON'T WANT THAT TO HAPPEN.
WE NEED TO GET RUSSELL OUT OF
THIS GAME IMMEDIATELY.
>> RUSSELL IS NOT A THREAT--
>> I DISAGREE COMPLETELY.
HE'S GOT HIS HOOKS
IN ONE OF THEM.
>> WHO DOES HE HAVE
HIS HOOKS IN?
>> STEPHANIE.
>> WHAT DOES HE DO EVERY TIME?
HE TAKES A CUTE LITTLE GIRL--
>> CUTE LITTLE GIRL-- AND TAKES
HER AND TURNS HER
INTO THE VILLAINESS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> I WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
>> I DON'T THINK WE
CAN LET IT HAPPEN.
I LIKE DAVID.
DAVID SEEMS LIKE A NICE GUY.
HE TOLD ME RUSSELL HAD HIS HOOKS
IN STEPHANIE.
ANY PROS OF HAVING RUSSELL
AROUND HAVE QUICKLY EVAPORATED.
HE'S JUST GOING TO SPREAD
PARANOIA AND BE A CANCER
TO THE TRIBE.
AT THIS POINT, THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE DONE YET EXCEPT FOR THE
TASK AT HAND WHICH IS GET
RUSSELL GONE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> WE WERE IN A TIME WARP.
>> I DON'T WANT TO HAVE ROB
STICK AROUND THAT LONG.
I MEAN, I LIKE THE GUY.
HE'S A GREAT GUY, BUT HE'S
DANGEROUS TO HAVE ON THE TRIBE.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE
GREASED LIGHTNING.
>> I'M WORKING ON...
( LAUGHTER )
DREADS.
>> THE GUYS ARE IN AWE OF ROB,
AND, YOU KNOW, HE'S GOING AFTER
ALL THE YOUNG GIRLS BECAUSE
THEY'RE EASY PICKINGS.
SO WHATEVER I DO, I THINK HE'S
PROBABLY WHO I'M GOING TO TRY
AND FOCUS ON REALLY QUICKLY.
IF THERE'S AN IDOL OUT THERE, IF
I AT ALL CAN DO ANYTHING TO FIND
ONE, THEN I WILL DO IT.
IF ANYONE CAN DO IT ON THIS
TRIBE, IT'S ME.
♪ ♪
>> MY IMMUNITY IDOL ANTENNA HAVE
BEEN ON ALERT SINCE I HIT
THE BEACH.
LIKE, I WANTED TO FIND IT.
I KNEW IT WAS HERE.
EVEN IF IT STOOD OUT IN OUR
CAMP, I WANTED TO LOOK AROUND
AND POKE AROUND.
I KNEW THAT IN ORDER FOR US TO
FIND IT, WE HAD TO FIND
LANDMARKS.
OUR LANDMARKS WERE GOING TO BE
OUR MAP.
>> SWEET.
THIS IS AWESOME.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
HO-HO-HO.
ROB'S GOOD.
I'M GOOD, TOO.
IT'S GOING TO BE FUN.
THIS IS GOING TO BE FUN.
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS, I
MEAN, IT MEANS POWER.
I'M PROBABLY GOING TO TELL
SOMEBODY ABOUT IT, BUT I HAVEN'T
DECIDED WHO YET.
BUT I CAN MAKE THIS BIG GIANT
SPLASH OF A MOVE AND, LIKE, GET
RID OF ROB TONIGHT
IF I WANTED TO.
I REALLY COULD.
THE FASTER HE GOES, THE BETTER.
>> HE'S NUMBER ONE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK, IN MY MIND.
>> ARE YOU ON BOARD?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> DON'T SAY A WORD.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU HOW
TO PLAY THE GAME.
LIKE RIGHT NOW YOU DECIDED TO DO
WHAT YOU WANTED TO DO AND I
APPRECIATE THAT.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU
HOW TO PLAY YOUR GAME.
IF I FEEL THE NEED TO TELL
SOMEBODY SOMETHING, I'LL DO IT.
I'M A VERY PROCESSED PERSON SO
IF YOU CAME TO ME AND SAID,
"LOOK, WE WANT TO FORM THIS
ALLIANCE AND WE WANT YOU TO BE A
PART OF IT AND WE WANT YOU TO
VOTE OUT ROB."
I'M GOING TO HEAR IT FOR WHAT IT
IS AND THEN I'M GOING TO STEP
BACK AND I'M GOING TO GO THROUGH
HOW YOU GOT THERE.
IT'S CALLED CORROBORATION.
TELL ME WHO THE OTHER VOTES ARE?
>> PHILLIP, RELAX.
>> JUST ANSWER MY QUESTION.
>> I'M SORRY WE SAID ANYTHING.
>> RIGHT NOW YOU DON'T HAVE
VOTE, PER THREE OF US.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
>> YOU NEED TO INFORM ME.
>> THE FACT THAT YOU'RE GETTING
THIS AT ATTITUDE WITH US.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE HAVING THAT
ATTITUDE WITH US.
>> THAT ATTITUDE IS NOT--
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU NEED TO PIPE THAT.
YOU NEED TO PIPE THAT THING
ABOUT AN ATTITUDE.
I'M A GROWN MAN.
I'M 52 YEARS OLD.
I'VE BEEN AROUND.
I'VE BEEN AN AGENT LIKE I TOLD
YOU BEFORE AND WHAT I LEARNED
THROUGHOUT MY CAREER
IS YOU ASK QUESTIONS.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY INFORMATION
TO GIVE YOU.
>> I DON'T NEED TWO PEOPLE
TALKING AT ONCE.
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY.
YOU GO, CHRISTINA, I'LL WAIT.
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO TALK
WHILE YOU'RE TALKING.
>> RIGHT NOW,
THERE ARE THREE PEOPLE.
I'M NOT GOING TO GO UP AND JUST
FOR THE HELL OF IT SAY, "ROB,"
AND THE REST OF THEM GO,
"PHILLIP."
THEY'VE STILL GOT THE VOTES
TO GET ME OUT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
HERE THEY COME.
WE HAD AN AGREEMENT TO WAIT AND
TALK ABOUT THIS UNTIL WE LOST.
WE'RE YOUR FRIEND HERE.
>> WE'RE DONE.
WE'RE DONE WITH THIS
CONVERSATION FOR NOW.
ALL RIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW IT HAPPENED.
HOW DID I GET STUCK WITH THE OLD
ANNOYING GUY IN THE DROOPY
FUCHSIA BRIEFS?
HE'S SUCH A PAIN IN MY ASS.
DID I MENTION THAT WE'RE IN AN
ALLIANCE TOGETHER?
HOW AWESOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
ON MY GO, EACH TRIBE WILL PUSH
FOUR BLOCKS ALONG THE TRACK TO
BUILD THE BASE OF A TEMPLE.
YOU'LL THEN RUN UP THE STEPS,
WHERE ONE PERSON WILL USE AN AXE
TO CHOP A SERIES OF ROPES,
RELEASING ANOTHER SET OF STEPS.
YOU'LL THEN MAKE YOUR WAY TO THE
TOP, WHERE YOU WILL RACE TO
COMPLETE A BLOCK PUZZLE,
COMPLETING YOUR TEMPLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE FIRST
PERSON SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT
RIGHT HERE.
THIS LITTLE STATUE GUARANTEES
YOUR SAFETY IN THIS GAME.
WHEN YOU'RE IN POSSESSION OF
IMMUNITY, YOU CAN'T BE
VOTED OUT.
WITHOUT IT, YOU ARE VULNERABLE.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNING TRIBE
WINS FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
ALL RIGHT, GIVE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE, AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO!
FOR IMMUNITY AND FIRE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT FOUR
BLOCKS.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THEM TO THIS
WALL ONE AT A TIME.
THEY ARE VERY HEAVY.
ZAPATERA WITH A BIT OF A LEAD
RIGHT OUT OF THE GATE.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> Jeff: GOTTA HIT THE WALL.
GO!
OMETEPE, YOU'RE GOOD.
LET'S GO, GUYS.
COME ON!
>> PUSH ON THAT SIDE.
>> PUSH!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY'S GOT TO
WORK TOGETHER.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: A VERY DECEIVING
CHALLENGE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THESE WOULD JUST
GLIDE OVER THESE TRACKS BUT
THEY DON'T.
OMETEPE SLOWING DOWN.
ZAPATERA STILL WITH A BIT
OF A LEAD.
YOU'RE GOOD!
OMETEPE DIG IN!
LET'S GO!
>> PUSH IT, BABY, PUSH IT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD!
ZAPATERA DOING A VERY GOOD JOB.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> Jeff: STRENGTH REALLY
MAKING A DIFFERENCE FOR
ZAPATERA.
>> GOT IT!
PUSH!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA HAS THEIR
THIRD BLOCK!
>> COME ON, GUYS, WE GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: OMETEPE REALLY
SLOWING DOWN.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: KEEP DIGGING!
>> PUSH!
>> GO!
>> Jeff: LET'S GO, OMETEPE.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
PUSH!
LET'S CATCH THEM.
COME ON, KEEP GOING.
GO, GO, GO!
>> DRIVE!
GO.
>> PUSH!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA,
YOU'RE GOOD.
GO.
OMETEPE HAS THEIR LAST BLOCK.
THEY HAVE FALLEN BEHIND.
>> LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
>> COME ON, GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: RALPH WORKING
ON THE ROPE NOW.
>> COME ON, RALPH!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE COMPLETELY
OUT OF IT RIGHT NOW.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: RALPH NOT WASTING
ANY TIME.
ZAPATERA WITH A BIG LEAD.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> KEEP IT GOING.
KEEP GOING.
COME ON NOW, DON'T QUIT.
>> Jeff: YOU WANT TO SEE THE
PATTERN ON THE OUTSIDE
OF THIS PURPLE.
YOU WANT THE SOLID COLORS
TO BE ON THE INSIDE.
>> THE BOTTOM CORNER.
>> Jeff: OMETEPE STILL PUSHING
THEIR LAST BLOCK.
YOU'RE GOOD.
LET'S GO, OMETEPE.
>> COME ON, MATT, COME ON!
>> Jeff: MATT WORKING ON THE
ROPES FOR OMETEPE.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: YOU BETTER
PICK IT UP, BROTHER!
>> THERE YOU GO, MATT.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> PERFECT!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA WORKING ON
THEIR PUZZLE
WITH A BIG HEAD START.
>> OKAY, WE GOT THIS, COME ON.
>> Jeff: MATT WORKING HIS WAY
THROUGH THOSE ROPES.
HE'S GOT ONE LEFT.
THERE IT IS!
LET'S GO!
YOU'RE STILL IN THIS!
>> COME ON, BABY!
>> Jeff: OMETEPE HAS A GREAT
PUZZLE MAKER IN ROB.
IS ROB STRONG ENOUGH TO BRING
HIS TRIBE BACK?
>> TELL US WHAT TO DO.
>> Jeff: DAVID BARKING
THE ORDERS
FOR ZAPATERA.
>> THIS ONE GOES RIGHT HERE.
>> Jeff: ROB IS LEADING
OMETEPE, AS EXPECTED.
>> HELP ME GET THIS OUT.
>> Jeff: OMETEPE IS NOT
PANICKING.
THEY'RE WORKING TOGETHER.
>> PERFECT.
>> HEY!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA HAD A
GIGANTIC LEAD.
AND IT IS GONE.
>> GUYS, GUYS, WE GOT THIS.
>> STAY IN IT.
>> I'M LISTENING TO HIM.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL IS NOW
CALLING THE SHOTS.
IT IS RUSSELL AND BOSTON ROB.
THIS IS WHERE PATIENCE AND
EXPERIENCE COMES INTO PLAY.
>> COME GET THIS PIECE.
>> Jeff: NOBODY WANTS TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
NOBODY WANTS TO GO
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THIS COULD BE A VERY CLOSE
FINISH.
>> COME ON, COME ON!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL SLIDES IN
ANOTHER PIECE.
ARE THEY RIGHT?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ZAPATERA WINS
IMMUNITY.
>> YES, BABY!
YES! YES!
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
ZAPATERA!
>> Jeff: CONGRATULATIONS,
ZAPATERA.
FIRST IMMUNITY WIN.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM ZAPATERA.
IN ADDITION, FIRE WILL GET A
WHOLE LOT EASIER.
ZAPATERA, GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ALL RIGHT, OMETEPE, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY FROM YOUR TRIBE WILL BE
THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME, THE FIRST PERSON SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> WE ARE STRONGER
THAN THEY ARE.
WE'RE FASTER THAN THEY ARE.
WE'RE SMARTER THAN THEY ARE.
I KNOW HOW BOSTON ROB THINKS.
RIGHT NOW, HE'S THINKING
OH, CRAP.
I'M STUCK WITH A BUNCH
OF WEENIES.
>> YEAH, SO WE LOST THE FIRST
CHALLENGE TODAY, WHICH TOTALLY
SUCKS, AND IN A WAY, LIKE, I
DON'T KNOW IF OTHER PEOPLE FEEL
THIS WAY, BUT I FEEL LIKE WE
LET ROB DOWN.
IT'S WEIRD, BUT YOU WANT TO
PLEASE YOUR LEADER, I GUESS.
BUT IT SUCKS WE HAVE TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
>> I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> I HAVE A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
>> I FOUND IT.
>> WHERE?
>> I JUST FOUND IT.
>> WHEN DID YOU GET A CLUE?
>> I DIDN'T GET A CLUE.
I FOUND IT WITHOUT A CLUE.
BUT, LISTEN, WHAT I THINK WE
SHOULD DO, AFTER CAREFULLY
THINKING ABOUT EVERYTHING, I
DON'T KNOW IF WE CAN TRUST
THE GIRLS.
I THINK WE SHOULD GET ALL THE
MEN TO VOTE FOR ME.
YOU, ME, AND BIG MOUTH OVER
THERE ALL VOTE FOR ROB.
AND THEY TRY AND VOTE ME OUT,
AND I'LL PLAY THE IDOL, AND
BOOM, LIKE THIS WHOLE GAME
TURNS.
>> YEAH, WOW.
YOU HAVE THE IDOL?
>> YEAH.
OKAY?
SO I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU
TOO LONG.
BUT I THINK THIS IS
OUR ONLY OPTION.
>> I WAS TOTALLY SHOCKED THAT
KRISTINA HAD THE IDOL, BUT I'M
AMAZED AND IT'S TOTALLY
MADE MY DAY.
SO SHE'S REALLY-- SHE WAS REALLY
EXCITED ABOUT USING IT TO
BLINDSIDE ROB TONIGHT.
AND AS MUCH AS IT IS, LIKE, A
FUN AND THAT WOULD BE AMAZING
AND FEEL REALLY AWESOME IN THE
MOMENT, HE IS A STRONG
COMPETITOR, AND WE STILL
NEED HIM.
IT'S YOUR IMMUNITY IDOL SO, YOU
KNOW, WHATEVER YOU WANT TO DO.
BUT I THINK THAT NATALIE IS THE
WEAKEST ONE.
I THINK THAT IF WE DO ROB
TONIGHT, EVERYONE IS GOING TO BE
PISSED OFF.
WE DON'T HAVE NUMBERS.
IT'S STILL JUST YOU ME-- YOU,
ME, AND PHILLIP.
THAT DOESN'T GET US ANYWHERE.
I'M GOING TO DO WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO.
I JUST WANT YOU TO THINK
ABOUT IT.
I DON'T WANT US TO COMMIT TO IT
RIGHT NOW JUST BECAUSE-- JUST
REALLY, REALLY THINK ABOUT IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, TENTATIVELY
WE'LL DO NATALIE.
LET ME PONDER IT
FOR A FEW MINUTES.
>> THINK ABOUT IT.
WE HAVE TIME.
JUST KNOW YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> I KNOW I'M NOT GOING HOME
THAT I'VE KNOWN FOR A WHILE.
VOTING NATALIE IS BETTER
FOR THE TRIBE.
VOTING ROB IS BETTER FOR ME.
THERE ARE SO MANY DIFFERENT WAYS
TO GO.
I WOULD LOVE TO VOTE ROB OFF
TONIGHT.
I WOULD LOVE TO.
I WOULD JUST LOVE TO.
JUST LIKE-- NEAH!
YOU KNOW.
HEY, WHO ARE YOU GUYS
THINKING OF
VOTING FOR TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M OPEN TO DISCUSSION.
>> WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ORIGINALLY, I WANTED TO VOTE
FRANCESCA OFF BECAUSE THE VERY
FIRST TIME I MET HER, SHE STOOD
UP ON THE MAT, LOOKED AT JEFF,
AND SAID, "I DON'T WANT TO PLAY
WITH HIM BECAUSE HE'S
TOO SNEAKY."
SHE KNOWS MY GAME SO I DON'T
WANT SOMEONE LIKE THAT
ON MY TRIBE.
BUT AFTER THINKING ABOUT IT SOME
MORE, THE SECOND WE LANDED ON
OUR BEACH, KRISTINA WAS THE ONE
LOOKING THROUGH ALL THE
SUPPLIES, LOOKING FOR THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
SHE'S DANGEROUS.
SHE KNOWS STRATEGY.
SHE KNOWS TO GET OUT THERE
AND WORK FOR IT.
TO ME, I DON'T NEED SOMEONE
LIKE THAT WITH ME.
>> I'LL TELL YOU THIS-- THE
SECOND WE LANDED ON THE BEACH,
CHRISTINA, THE FIRST THING SHE
DID, SHE WAS LOOKING THROUGH THE
SEWING KIT.
>> I KNOW, THAT'S WHAT I
THOUGHT.
>> I WOULDN'T PUT IT PAST HER
TO HAVE IT?
>> TO HAVE IT?
>> I THINK THEY HAVE IT.
>> I THINK THEY HAVE IT, AND
EVEN IF THEY DON'T, THERE'S NO
REASON WHY WE SHOULDN'T SPLIT
THE VOTE AND BE SAFE, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
THE GUYS ARE VOTING FOR
FRANCINE-- YEAH, FRANCESCA.
WE'RE VOTING FOR FRAN.
YOU GUYS ARE VOTING FOR
CHRISTINE.
>> DOES EVERYBODY UNDERSTAND
THAT?
I GOT SO SCREWED LAST SEASON
BECAUSE ONE PERSON DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND.
>> GO THROUGH IT AGAIN.
>> DON'T LET ANYBODY TRY TO,
LIKE -- BAMBOOZLE YOU.
>> YEAH, THAT'S IT.
THIS IS US.
THAT'S IT.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> WHEN YOU'RE IN THIS-- WHAT I
CALL THE HYPER STATE OF AROUSAL,
WHEN YOU'RE IN A SURVIVOR
ENVIRONMENT, YOU'RE LOSING
WEIGHT, YOU'RE THIRSTY, YOU'RE
SUFFERING FROM DEHYDRATION,
THINGS CAN SOMETIMES FLARE UP,
AND WHAT HAVE YOU.
BUT I REALIZE I STILL HAVEN'T
GOTTEN THE ANSWER THAT I
ORIGINALLY SAID TO YOU, AS WELL
AS TO FRANCESCA, WHICH IS I'M
WITH YOU, IF I KNOW WHO THAT
OTHER VOTES ARE--
>> ALL RIGHT, PHIL, COME ON.
COME HERE.
>> I'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
>> NO, NO.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
>> ALL RIGHT, SHOW ME.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU DON'T NEED THE VOTES.
WE'VE GOT THEM RIGHT HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS?
THIS IS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
WHAT IT MEANS IS THAT YOURS,
MINE, AND FRANCESCA'S VOTES WILL
DECIDE WHO GOES HOME.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
I'M EXTREMELY NERVOUS TELLING
PHILLIP ABOUT THE IDOL.
HE CAME UP TO ME AND SAID, "I'VE
DONE MY ANALYTICAL THING, AND WE
DON'T HAVE THE VOTES--" I DIDN'T
WANT HIM TO SWITCH OR DO
SOMETHING WEIRD.
I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T TRUST THE
GUY, AND THAT'S WHY I HATED
TELLING HIM.
I JUST FELT I HAD TO TELL HIM.
I DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE THERE.
HE HAD TO GET SOME REASSURANCE,
THAT HE HAS SOME POWER HERE
IN THIS GAME.
WITH YOUR BRAIN AND, LIKE, THE
WAY YOU THINK, AND, I MEAN, JUST
YOU HELPING ME AND-- WE COULD GO
ALL THE WAY IF WE WANTED TO.
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
YOU HAVE MY SUPPORT.
>> OKAY, COOL.
ANOTHER HUG.
>> HOPEFULLY HE'LL JUST KEEP A
LID ON IT.
THAT WAS A RISK.
HE CAN'T HANDLE THE INFORMATION.
HE CAN'T KEEP IT ON THE DOWNLOW.
HE'S A SPAZ ABOUT IT.
HE'S A SPAZ ABOUT EVERYTHING, IF
YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW
THE TRUTH.
OH, GOD.
>> IN THE TRIBE'S BEST INTEREST,
IT MAY NOT NECESSARILY BE THE
BEST INTEREST TO GET RID OF ROB.
BUT IS IT IN THE INTEREST OF
PHILLIP SHEPPARD AND COMPANY WHO
CAME TO PLAY A GAME AND MAKE
SOME BOLD MOVES?
AND I THINK THE LONGER ROB IS
AROUND AND SOLIDIFYING THOSE
GIRLS AND THAT WHOLE THING, I'M
WEAKENED, AND SO I NEED TO GET
RID OF HIM NOW.
GOOD-BYE, ROB.
AND YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THE NEW LEADER.
OF OUR TRIBE.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU
IS A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH
AND APPROACH THE FLAME.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL, BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIVE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE
YOU, WITH A SLIGHT EXCEPTION
THIS SEASON, REDEMPTION ISLAND,
WHICH WE WILL TALK ABOUT.
ALL RIGHT, ROB, WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU FIRST GET TO CAMP?
>> RIGHT TO WORK.
RIGHT AWAY.
PHILLIP SET THE TONE.
EVERYBODY'S PITCHING IN.
AND WE'VE GOT A PRETTY DAMN GOOD
SHELTER BUILT THE FIRST NIGHT.
>> Jeff: SO, PHILLIP, DID YOU
JUST NATURALLY ASSUME THE
LEADERSHIP ROLE?
>> NOT NECESSARILY THE
LEADERSHIP ROLE, BUT IF I SEE
WORK THAT NEEDS TO BE DONE, I'LL
SUGGEST IT.
>> Jeff: SO, MATT, IS PHILLIP
THE LEADER FOR NOW AROUND CAMP?
>> I MEAN, IF YOU'RE DOING
SOMETHING THAT IS
COUNTER-PRODUCTIVE, HE'LL CALL
YOU OUT ON IT.
AND IT'S NOT WELL RECEIVED ON
THE VERY FIRST DAY.
>> Jeff: FRANCESCA, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE DIFFERENT REASONS YOU
MIGHT VOTE SOMEONE OUT TONIGHT.
>> WE NEED TO KEEP THE TRIBE AS
PHYSICALLY STRONG AS POSSIBLE.
AND SO, THAT IMPLIES THAT A
WOMAN IS GOING TO GO, BUT, I
MEAN, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
WAIT AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> Jeff: KRISTINA, HOW ARE YOU
FEELING TONIGHT GOING
INTO THE VOTE?
>> I DON'T FEEL SAFE AT ALL.
I HAVE MY STUFF RIGHT HERE
BECAUSE THERE'S A VERY GOOD
POSSIBILITY I'M GOING
TO GO HOME.
>> Jeff: ROB, A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT THE GUYS HAVING
A FREE PASS.
I WOULD PUT AN ASTERISK
NEXT TO YOUR NAME.
>> OF COURSE.
IT COULD BE ME WALKING AWAY, AND
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO ABOUT
IT, BUT THAT'S THE GAME.
>> Jeff: FRANCESCA, LET'S TALK
ABOUT REDEMPTION ISLAND.
NOW WHEN YOU VOTE SOMEBODY OUT,
THEY COULD COME BACK TO EITHER
HELP OR HAUNT YOU.
>> OH, YEAH.
IT'S DEFINITELY ADDING A LEVEL
OF COMPLEXITY AND IT COMPLETELY
CHANGES THE GAME.
IF BOSTON ROB GOT VOTED OUT
TONIGHT-- WHICH HE'S NOT GOING
TO-- BUT IF HE DID, HE WOULD
PROBABLY BE FINE.
WE COULD ALL FEEL THERE'S A GOOD
CHANCE HE'S GOING TO COME BACK
INTO THE GAME.
>> I HAVE AN ISSUE WITH THAT
STATEMENT SHE JUST MADE BECAUSE
FRANCESCA AND KRISTINA ASKED ME
TO CAST MY VOTE FOR ROB.
>> THAT IS NOT TRUE.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> I ASKED YOU TO--
>> EXCUSE ME, I DIDN'T INTERRUPT
YOU WHILE YOU SPOKE.
I WANT TO FINISH WHAT I WAS
SAYING.
>> KRISTINA, DID I ASK HIM
TO VOTE FOR ROB?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> EXCUSE ME!
EXCUSE ME.
>> YOU ARE A CRAZY PERSON.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> I'M GOING TO INTERRUPT
YOU, PHILLIP.
I DON'T RESPECT YOU.
I'M GOING TO SAY WHAT I WANT TO
SAY WHEN I WANT TO SAY IT.
>> JEFF, I'M A FORMER
SPECIAL AGENT SO IF I MAKE A
STATEMENT TO YOU I'LL MAKE SURE
TO ADHERE TO THAT
AND I WILL NOT BETRAY.
I'LL GO DOWN ON A SINKING SHIP
BEFORE I DO THAT UNTIL I HEAR
SOMETHING DIFFERENT AND I JUST
HEARD SOMETHING DIFFERENT SO MY
VOTE TONIGHT WILL BE FOR
FRANSESQUA.
>> FRANCESCA.
>> I DON'T WANT PHILLIP TO JUMP
DOWN MY THROAT NOW, BUT PHILLIP
JUST KIND OF HAD
A MAJOR FREAKOUT
OUT OF NOWHERE AND IT PUTS
INTO PEOPLE'S MINDS THAT
MAYBE THERE'S A LITTLE BIT OF
INSTABILITY THERE.
>> EXCUSE ME, YOU AND
FRANSQUES-- FRAN--
>> "CESCA."
>> FRANCESCA APPROACHED ME
TO GO ALONG WITH
THEM BECAUSE SHE HAS
AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
AND THAT'S WHY THEY APPROACH
ME WITH IT.
THEY TOOK ME TO IT
AND THEY SHOWED IT TO ME.
>> Jeff: SO, KRISTINA,
YOU DO HAVE AN IDOL?
>> I DO HAVE AN IDOL.
>> Jeff: WHO IS THAT NEWS TO?
>> I DIDN'T KNOW.
>> WE DIDN'T KNOW.
>> SO THAT WAS THE PLAN, YOU TWO
WERE GOING TO GET TOGETHER
AND VOTE ME OFF.
>> NO.
>> YES, ROB.
>> I HAVEN'T HEARD YOU DEFEND
YOURSELF.
>> I HAD NO INTENTION OF VOTING
YOU OUT, AND KRISTINA, CAN YOU
ATTEST TO THAT.
>> THAT'S ABSOLUTELY TRUE.
>> PHILLIP.
>> I TOLD HIM THAT I WAS GOING
TO VOTE FOR YOU, BUT I WAS
ACTUALLY GOING TO VOTE
FOR NATALIE.
>> EXCUSE ME, ROB.
YOU JUST HEARD WHAT SHE SAID.
I HAD NO KNOWLEDGE WHAT SHE WAS
REALLY GOING TO DO.
AND NOW YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY
I'M UNSTABLE.
NO, I'M QUITE RATIONAL.
AND GUESS WHAT, I WAS GOING TO
VOTE FOR FRANSQUESCA--
>> FRANCESCA.
>> MY MOUTH IS DRY AND I'VE BEEN
GETTING TREATMENT FOR IT.
I'M DONE, JEFF, I HAVE NOTHING
FURTHER TO ADD.
>> Jeff: NOTHING?
>> I'M DONE WITH IT.
>> Jeff: ROB, YOU HAVE TO BE
SITTING THERE THINKING
WHO DO I BELIEVE?
>> PHILLIP IS PRETTY ADAMANT
ABOUT HIS STORY.
FRANCESCA HAS ADAMANTLY
DENIED IT.
KRISTINA REALLY HASN'T DEFENDED
HERSELF AT ALL-- YOU HAVEN'T.
>> IT WAS SOMETHING THAT WE
CONSIDERED.
WE WOULD BE IDIOTS NOT TO.
BUT IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT WE
WERE GOING TO DO TONIGHT.
>> YOU HAVE THE IMMUNITY IDOL?
LET ME SEE IT.
THIS IS THE IMMUNITY IDOL?
>> YES.
>> AND YOU'RE SAYING
THAT HE'S LYING.
>> YES.
>> OKAY, GIVE ME
THE IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU'LL STAY.
GIVE ME THE IMMUNITY IDOL, AND
YOU'LL STAY.
WHY SHOULD I TRUST YOU ANY MORE
THAN YOU SHOULD TRUST ME.
>> I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> I'M JUST STAYING BY YOU NOT
GIVING IT TO ME IT MAKES ME
THINK THAT YOU'RE NOT TELLING
THE TRUTH.
>> THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> IT'S YOURS.
OBVIOUSLY, SOMEBODY'S LYING.
SO YOU HAVE AN IDOL AND IT MAY
SAVE YOU FOR THREE MORE DAYS.
BUT... I'M GOING TO DO WHAT I
SAID I WAS GOING TO DO WITH THE
PEOPLE THAT I SAID I WAS GOING
TO DO IT WITH.
AND THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: THIS HAS BEEN ONE OF
THE MOST AMAZING
TRIBAL COUNCILS.
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA WHAT
IS ABOUT TO GO DOWN.
LET'S GET TO THE VOTE.
ANDREA, YOU'RE UP.
>> MAN, IT FEELS SO GOOD TO PLAY
WITH YOU AMATEURS.
YOU GIVE AWAY SO MUCH.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ENOUGH TO
KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
THANKS FOR THE MEMORIES.
>> YOU MIGHT MAKE IT THROUGH
THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL, BUT
PROBABLY NOT THE NEXT ONE.
>> I HAD PLANNED ON VOTING FOR
YOU OR BOSTON ROB TONIGHT, BUT
YOUR CRAZY OUTBURST
HAS SPARED NATALIE.
I HOPE TO NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KRISTINA.
KRISTINA.
THAT'S TWO VOTES KRISTINA.
FRANCESCA.
ONE VOTE FRANCESCA.
PHILLIP.
ONE VOTE PHILLIP.
FRANCESCA.
TWO VOTES FRANCESCA.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP, TWO VOTES
KRISTINA, TWO VOTES FRANCESCA.
KRISTINA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES KRISTINA.
TIED AGAIN.
THREE VOTES FRANCESCA, THREE
VOTES KRISTINA, TWO VOTES
PHILLIP.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,"
FRANCESCA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
FRANCESCA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO
RE-ENTER THIS GAME.
TAKE YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> GOOD-BYE, YOU GUYS.
DON'T TRUST PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: WELL, GOOD NEWS,
FLINT WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME
ON "SURVIVOR":
RUSSELL MEETS HIS MATCH.
>> I DON'T LIKE HOW YOU ARE
COMING AT ME.
I KNOW HOW TO PLAY THIS GAME.
>> THIS OLD BOY OUT HERE DOES,
TOO.
>> Jeff: AND PHILLIP MEETS HIS.
WHILE AT REDEMPTION ISLAND,
EVERY WEEK IS A FIGHT
TO STAY ALIVE.
THIS IS IT, DO OR DIE TIME.
THIS IS THE FIRST STEP IN YOUR
JOURNEY TO GET EVEN.
TO GET A SECOND CHANCE
IN THIS GAME.
>> WOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE TRUSTED MY
INSTINCTS FROM THE BEGINNING,
WHICH WAS, YOU KNOW, THAT
PHILLIP WASN'T SOMEONE
TO BE TRUSTED.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN THE NEXT
PERSON COMES TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE DUEL
IS GOING TO ENTAIL.