>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> JEFF, I'M A FORMER
SPECIAL AGENT.
>> YOU ARE A CRAZY PERSON.
>> Jeff: BEFORE THE MERGE,
BOTH TRIBES WERE RIFE
WITH INFIGHTING.
>> DAVID UNDER PRESSURE
IS REALLY STRESSING.
>> YOU'RE WRONG THERE.
DON'T EVEN GO THERE WITH THAT.
I DON'T FREAK OUT.
>> Jeff: BUT AFTER THE MERGE,
THE FORMER OMETEPE TRIBE AND THE
FORMER ZAPATERA TRIBE SET ASIDE
THEIR INTERNAL SQUABBLES BUT
STAYED DIVIDED
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
>> I WANT MY GROUP
TO HATE ZAPATERA.
>> Jeff: AND MATT WAS CAUGHT
BETWEEN THE TWO SO ROB
IMMEDIATELY TOOK HIM OUT.
>> HE CAN'T BE TRUSTED SO
BECAUSE OF THAT, I'M GIVING HIM
A ONE-WAY TICKET BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> WHAT THE HELL, GUYS.
>> Jeff: DOWN 6-5, THE FORMER
ZAPATERA HATCHED
A DESPERATE PLAN.
>> WE TOSSED AROUND THE IDEA OF
TRYING TO SEE IF WE CAN WOO
SOME OF THE OMETEPE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: AT BACK-TO-BACK
TRIBAL COUNCILS THEY TRIED TO
CONVINCE THE OMETEPE LOW MAN
TO JUMP SHIP.
DAVID, OF THE SIX,
WHO IS ON THE BOTTOM?
>> WE THINK PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: BUT PHILLIP WOULDN'T
BUDGE AND PLAYED
THE HONOR AND DUTY CARD.
>> I SERVED IN THE
UNITED STATES ARMY
AND HAD THE SECOND
HIGHEST MEDAL
THEY GIVE DURING PEACE TIME.
>> GIVE IT UP.
>> I DON'T HAVE TO GIVE IT UP.
>> YOU SOUND LIKE A LUNATIC.
>> PHILLIP NEVER CEASES
TO AMAZE ME.
>> Jeff: SO MIKE WAS VOTED OUT.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND SO WAS DAVID.
YOU WILL NOW HEAD TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THE GAME.
ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: GOOD LUCK.
NOW RALPH, JULIE, AND STEVE FACE
A UNITED OMETEPE TRIBE
WHILE FOR THE FIRST TIME
THREE COMPETITORS FACE A DUEL
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> I CAN'T SLEEP.
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW I'M
GOING TO PULL MYSELF UP BY MY
BOOTSTRAPS AND KEEP MY SANITY.
I JUST LICKED MY WOUNDS
AND BLEED FOR A LITTLE WHILE
AND HURT, BUT I WAS READY
TO KIND OF
GET IN THE MINDSET OF ALL RIGHT,
REDEMPTION ISLAND, PART TWO.
LET'S DO IT.
AND THEN CURVEBALL.
>> GOD, MY BROTHER
WOULDN'T QUIT.
MY DAD WOULDN'T QUIT.
YOU WOULD NEVER QUIT,
LORD JESUS,
AND YOUR SPIRIT LIVES IN ME.
>> TO MY ARRIVAL
AT REDEMPTION ISLAND
MATT AND MIKE ARE BOTH
STILL HERE SO LET'S SEE
IF I CAN MAKE SOME NOISE HERE
AND MAYBE GET BACK
INTO THE GAME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> IT'S MURPHY, DAVID MURPHY?
>> WHAT!
>> I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
WHERE AM I GOING?
>> WHAT IN THE WORLD, MAN?
WHAT...
DAVID ROLLS UP, AND, I MEAN,
MY MIND IS COMPLETELY
BLOWN AT THIS POINT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK.
LIKE, WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON.
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'RE--
WE HAVE TO HAVE A DUEL TOMORROW.
>> DUELS NOW ARE ALL
GOING TO BE THREE-PERSON DUELS.
>> OR WHAT IF THERE ISN'T--
I MEAN--
>> WHAT IF THIS IS THE LAST ONE?
>> I GUESS IF WE'RE ALREADY ALL
ON THE JURY-- THAT'S JUST WEIRD.
>> YEAH.
>> CAN YOU-- CAN YOU HAVE A DUEL
BETWEEN THREE PEOPLE?
>> THAT WOULD BE A TRIAL.
>> A TRUAL.
>> A TRUAL?
>> THIS IS CERTAINLY
AN INTERESTING CHOICE.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
TO MAKE OF IT.
WHO KNOWS WHAT
THE OTHER TWIST MAY BE.
WE DON'T KNOW IF THERE
WILL BE A DUEL
OR WHAT THE DUEL WILL BE
OR WHO WILL BE IN IT,
SO DEFINITELY LOOK FORWARD
TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
>> GOOD NIGHT, ZAPATERA.
>> GOOD NIGHT, TEAM ZAPATERA.
>> THE ZAPATERA REJECTS.
>> ISN'T THE SKIN GOOD?
>> YUMMY, HUH?
>> I'M GLAD MY MOOD
CHANGED AROUND.
I WAS REALLY HAPPY DAVE
WENT OFF INSTEAD OF ME.
I WASN'T READY TO GO YET.
>> HE DIDN'T HAVE MUCH TO SAY.
>> NO, THE WHOLE THING
WAS OCCUPIED BY PHIL.
>> UH-HUH.
>> FLAPPING HIS GUMS.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL LAST NIGHT
WAS SIX ON 4, NOW SIX ON THREE
AGAINST RALPH, JULIE AND I,
AND AFTER DAVE'S PERFORMED
SO WELL
THE LAST COUPLE OF CHALLENGES,
WE LOSE DAVE.
AND WE JUST THREW
ALL FOUR OF OURS AT ROB
AND WOMP-WOMP.
>> AND I JUST HAVEN'T REALLY
FIGURED PHILLIP OUT.
I CAN'T IMAGINE SOMEBODY
ALWAYS BEING THAT STRANGE.
PRETTY MUCH EVERYTHING
HE DOES BUGS US,
BUT THE REST OF OMETEPE
ARE STICKING TO HIM LIKE GLUE.
BOSTON ROB'S GOT THEM ALL
VERY TIGHT.
I'M NOT SURE IF PHILLIP IS EVEN
A GOOD GUY AT HEART,
BUT HE'S DOING HIS THING.
HE'S OUT HERE SURVIVING.
I TAKE MY HAT OFF TO HIM.
THE ONLY HOPE
WE CAN HANG OUR HAT ON
IS HOW IRRITATED THEY
COULD BE WITH PHILLIP.
THERE'S ALWAYS A CHANCE.
>> WHEN I GOT INTO BUDDHISM,
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT YOU LEARN
IS YOUR SPIRIT
IS INTERCONNECTED
TO EVERY SINGLE LIVING THING,
INCLUDING THE TATHAGATA,
WHICH YOU MIGHT CALL GOD
OR ALLAH OR BUDDHA.
IT WILL MANIFEST ITSELF
IN A NUMBER OF DIFFERENT WAYS.
YOU CAN HEAR IT.
YOU CAN FEEL IT.
AND YOU JUST HAVE
TO BE WILLING TO ACCEPT IT
FOR WHAT IT IS AND CHANNEL THAT.
I DID A MEDITATION THIS MORNING.
I WAS FOCUSING ON MY ANCESTORS.
YOU KNOW, I HAD A PREMONITION
THROUGH MY GRANDFATHER AND I
TOOK THAT AS AN INDICATION THAT
AS MY RELATIONSHIP WITH ROB.
I THINK IT HAS FINALLY COME TO
WHAT I CALL THE FULL CIRCLE
OF TRUST.
AND I'M GOING TO PLAY MY ROLE.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M NOT
PURSUING THE MILLION DOLLARS
BECAUSE I'LL BE HERE
AT THE END OF THE GAME.
>> IT'S READY.
DO YOU WANT TO EAT IT?
>> YEAH.
>> THE FOOD SITUATION FOR THE
OLD ZAPATERA TRIBE IS--
IS GREAT.
WE HAVE A TON OF RICE LEFT.
AND WE'RE EATING IT.
>> THERE'S SO MUCH RICE LEFT.
>> PRETTY GOOD.
>> AND WE'RE JUST GOING TO EAT
AND ENJOY AND AT LEAST
WE WON'T BE HUNGRY.
THE HUNGER HAS BEEN TOUGH
BUT WE'RE HAPPY NOW.
WE'RE HAPPY IN THE FOOD FIELD.
>> YOU GOOD?
>> YEAH, I'M GOOD.
>> YOU WERE JUST EATING
TO FINISH IT?
>> I WOULDN'T WANT IT
TO GO TO WASTE.
>> LIFE'S PRETTY GOOD, MAN.
>> THE RICE SITUATION
IS PRETTY UGLY.
THIS MORNING, JULIE WAS ABLE TO
SCOOP SEVEN AND A HALF SCOOPS OF
RICE OUT OF THAT COOKED POT.
IN OUR OLD TRIBE WE WOULD HAVE
TWO OF THOSE SEA SHELLS,
ONE, TWO.
DONE.
>> I WANT TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO GET EVEN.
>> I CONTEND THAT SHE'S TRYING
TO USE UP THE RICE
BEFORE THEY GO.
>> I PLAN ON SCOOPING QUITE A
BIT OF RICE
OUT OF THEIR TIN
AND PUTTING IT IN OURS.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS
ALL RICE HERE BELONGS
TO ALL OF US.
>> PHILLIP IS THE RICE POLICE.
>> I'M NOW WATCHING
THE ZAPATERA LIKE A LION.
IT'S TRIVIAL.
BUT, APPARENTLY, THAT'S THE
STATE OF THE WORLD TODAY
AND MURLONIO TRIBE.
>> PLEASE BE TREE MAIL.
PLEASE BE TREE MAIL.
>> WE GOT SOMETHING.
>> YAY!
>> "AS COMFORTABLE
AS YOU ALL MAY BE,
IT'S TIME AGAIN
FOR YOU ALL TO SEE
A BATTLE BETWEEN THOSE OUTCAST
WHO WILL LEAVE
AND WHO WILL LAST."
>> "TIME AGAIN FOR ALL TO SEE."
>> SWEET!
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS
FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
MATT, MIKE, AND DAVID.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
WE INVITED THE REST OF THE TRIBE
TO WITNESS YOUR DUEL.
MATT, BACK-TO-BACK BLINDSIDES.
WHERE'S YOUR EMOTIONAL
STATE OF MIND RIGHT NOW?
>> I NEVER KNEW THAT STRANGERS
COULD HURT ME SO DEEPLY.
UM, I MEAN, I GUESS SHAME ON ME
FOR LETTING THEM FOOL ME
TWICE, YOU KNOW.
IT HURTS, BUT I'M READY
TO KEEP GOING IF I CAN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SHOULD WE
GET TO TODAY'S DUEL?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
EACH OF YOU WILL HAVE
150 WOODEN TILES.
YOU WILL USE THOSE TILES
TO BUILD A HOUSE OF CARDS.
THE FIRST TWO TO REACH
EIGHT FEET STAY ALIVE.
LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD AND WILL
BECOME THE FIRST MEMBER
OF OUR JURY.
>> WOOO!
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY
TO GET TO THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
THE ONLY BASIC RULE IS YOU
CANNOT STACK THESE JUST FLAT
ONE ON TOP OF EACH OTHER.
YOU HAVE TO BUILD
A TRADITIONAL HOUSE OF CARDS.
>> Jeff: MIKE NOT
MESSING AROUND,
RIGHT AROUND THE SIX-FOOT MARK.
MATT AROUND THE FIVE-FOOT MARK.
>> OH, BOY.
>> Jeff: DAVID HOVERING
AROUND THREE FEET.
THIS STACK IS SO TALL, MIKE IS
NOW MOVING TO THE LADDER.
GETTING CLOSER AND CLOSER
TO THAT EIGHT-FOOT MARK.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE FIRST.
YOU JUST DON'T WANT TO BE LAST.
MIKE GETTING VERY CLOSE.
>> NICE, MIKE.
>> Jeff: ALMOST THERE.
ONE MORE STACK
WILL DO IT FOR MIKE.
IF HE CAN JUST REMAIN CALM.
MATT DOING VERY WELL.
DAVID CATCHING UP QUICKLY.
MIKE IS JUST SHORT.
THIS WILL DO IT.
GOTTA GET THAT TO LAY
ON ITS OWN.
MIKE FLIRTING WITH DISASTER,
BEING VERY CAREFUL,
DOES NOT WANT TO LOSE
THIS STACK.
NOT WITH MATT BREATHING
DOWN HIS NECK
AND DAVID RIGHT BEHIND.
DAVID IS NOW BACK IN IT.
DAVID'S ON HIS LADDER.
MATT GETTING CLOSER.
MIKE HAS A VERY TALL STACK.
JUST DOESN'T WANT TO LOSE IT.
MATT GETTING VERY CLOSE NOW
TO FINISHING.
DAVID GETTING CLOSER
MIKE IS LESS THAN A HALF
AN INCH AWAY.
GOTTA REACH THE TOP OF THE POST.
IF HE CAN STACK IT AND GET
HIS HANDS AWAY AND HE DOES.
MIKE IS GOOD.
MIKE STAYS ALIVE.
MATT IS VERY CLOSE.
CAN HE DO IT RIGHT HERE?
DAVID TRYING TO GET IN IT.
MATT DOES IT.
MIKE AND MATT STAY ALIVE!
( APPLAUSE )
>> NICE TRY, DAVE.
>> GOOD CHALLENGE, EVERYBODY.
>> GOOD TRY, DAVID.
>> NICE TRY, DAVE.
>> Jeff: MIKE, FIRST DUEL,
DID WHAT YOU HAD TO DO.
YOU STAY ALIVE.
>> IT FEELS GOOD.
THANK YOU, JEFF, THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: MATT, SEVEN STRAIGHT
DUELS YOU HAVE STAYED ALIVE.
SEIZING THAT MOMENT ONCE AGAIN.
DAVID, AFTER 25 VERY TOUGH DAYS
IN THIS GAME, YOUR SHOT
AT THE MONEY IS OVER.
YOU WILL RETURN TO THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL AS THE FIRST
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
YOU CAN TOSS YOUR BUFF
IN THE URN ON YOUR WAY OUT.
>> BYE, DAVID!
( APPLAUSE )
>> I SAW REDEMPTION ISLAND AS
A CHANCE TO FURTHER MYSELF
IN THE GAME.
UNFORTUNATELY, MY PLAN DIDN'T
WORK AS WELL AS I WOULD
LIKE FOR IT TO HAVE.
I THINK THIS HAS GIVEN ME
A REALLY FRESH OUTLOOK
AND DETERMINATION TO TACKLE
EVERYTHING I WANT TO DO AND JUST
VERY APPRECIATIVE FOR THAT.
>> DAVID'S GOING TO BE THE FIRST
MEMBER OF THE JURY.
WE'LL TRY TO SEND PEOPLE
TO THE DUEL
TO BEAT OTHER PEOPLE
WHO ARE ALREADY THERE--
NAMELY, MATT.
WE SENT MIKE AND WE SENT DAVID,
AND DAVID FAILED SO MATT
IS STILL IN THERE.
IF HE COMES BACK AND BEATS ME,
IT'S OVER.
>> Jeff: MATT AND MIKE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
YOU CAN HEAD BACK
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
AND AWAIT YOUR NEXT DUEL
AND YOUR NEXT OPPONENT.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> SEE YOU, GUYS.
>> GOD'S CONTINUED TO GIVE ME
THE STRENGTH DAY AFTER DAY.
HE'S GIVEN ME NEW HOPE, AND IF
IT'S HIS WILL,
THEN I'LL CONTINUE TO WIN.
AND TRY TO TAKE ROB OUT.
>> I WANT, LIKE, A POT.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
>> YEAH, LET'S DO IT.
♪ WE'VE GOT TO EAT
MORE THAN THE ♪
♪ OLD ZAPATERA TRIBE
RICE ROLLS ♪
♪ WE'RE GOING TO EAT OURSELVES ♪
♪ OUT OF HOUSE AND HOME
AFTER ONE DAY ♪
♪ RICE WARS. ♪
>> HEY!
>> THAT WAS GOOD, YOU GUYS.
>> OH, NO.
ROB, WE HAVE, LIKE, MAGGOTS
OR SOMETHING IN HERE.
>> WHAT?
>> I OPENED THE RICE, AND I
DISCOVERED THAT THERE WERE
SOME MAGGOTS.
>> SICK.
>> PHIL DECIDED HE WANTED TO
DUMP ALL THE RICE
ON TO A BLANKET.
SO WE SEPARATED THE MAGGOTS AND
WE DUMPED THE REST OF THE BAD
RICE INTO THE OCEAN.
>> LET'S PUT IT
IN THEIR CONTAINER
AND WE'LL JUST ALL USE
THE SAME CONTAINER.
>> THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO WANT TO DO THAT.
I WOULDN'T WANT TO DO THAT
IF I WERE THEM.
>> WE HAVE NOWHERE
TO PUT OUR RICE.
OUR RICE IS ON THE BLANKET WITH
ALL THE BUGS AND DIRT
GETTING INTO IT.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO EAT
FOR THE REST OF THE TIME?
>> BON APPETITE.
>> HOW NASTY MUST THAT BE.
>> OUR RICE IS ALL, LIKE--
THERE'S, LIKE, MAGGOTS
AND MOLD IN IT,
SO WE JUST DUMPED OUT
ALL THE GOOD RICE
AND SEPARATED IT.
COULD WE PUT ALL OF OUR RICE
IN YOURS?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
I DON'T THINK SO.
I DON'T THINK RALPH
WOULD GO FOR IT, EITHER.
>> I'LL TELL THEM.
>> I DON'T THINK SO, DO YOU?
>> NO.
>> IT'S AN EYE OPENER
TO SEE INDIVIDUALS
BEHAVE THE WAY THEY
ARE CURRENTLY BEHAVING,
EVEN IN A "GAME SURVIVOR"
ENVIRONMENT.
SO TO ME, YOU COULD PROBABLY
LEAVE HERE WITH SOME DAMAGES
POTENTIALLY TO SEE JUST HOW BAD
HUMAN BEINGS WILL CONDUCT
THEMSELVES IN AN ENVIRONMENT
LIKE THIS.
>> THE OTHER RICE
IS PERFECTLY FINE.
OUR CONTAINER HAD A LEAK
IN THE BOTTOM OF IT.
IT GOT WET AND IT MOLDED,
BUT THE RICE
THAT'S ON THAT TOWEL
IS PERFECTLY GOOD RICE.
THAT'S NOTHING WRONG WITH IT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I'M GOING TO TALK
ABOUT IT WITH RALPH.
>> LOOK, YOU GUYS
AREN'T BEING REASONABLE.
YOU SHOULD THINK ABOUT IT
LOGICALLY.
IT'S NOT A ZAPATERA DECISION.
IT'S OUR RICE.
ANYWAY, I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
THIS ARGUMENT.
ONCE THE TRIBES MERGED,
ONLY THE REWARDS ARE SEPARATE.
THAT'S THE WAY IT'S DONE.
>> WOULDN'T IT HAVE BEEN SMART
TO TALK ABOUT THIS
BEFORE YOU DUMPED IT
ALL OUT, PHILLIP?
>> NO, BUT I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
THAT DEBATE WITH YOU.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE THE RICE
OUTSIDE OF THE CONTAINER.
I ASKED, UNLESS YOU WALK
WITH THAT CAN,
THE FIRST OPPORTUNITY I HAVE
TO TAKE THAT CAN
AND HIDE IT, I WILL.
>> SO IN OTHER WORDS YOU'D
BE THREATENING MY TRIBE
WITH PHYSICALLY
TAKING SOMETHING.
>> YOU'RE THREATENING THE TRIBE
RIGHT NOW BY SAYING
GO AHEAD AND LET THAT
ON THE GROUND SPOIL.
THE LONGER IT IS OUT HERE
MOISTURE IS GETTING TO IT.
>> YOU ( BLEEP ).
>> I'LL PUT IT BLUNT TO YOU.
UNLESS YOU WALK WITH THAT
( BLEEP ) CAN EVERYWHERE YOU GO,
I'M GOING TO PUT
THE RICE IN THERE
AND YOU WILL COME ASK ME
FOR THE RICE.
I'M A VERY REASONABLE PERSON
TO DEAL WITH.
>> YOU'RE NOT REASONABLE
AT ALL, DUDE.
YOU'RE A ( BLEEP ) LUNATIC.
>> I KNOW I AM.
THAT'S THE ONE THING
YOU NEVER WANT TO FORGET.
>> YOU'RE A DANGEROUS MAN.
>> YOU NEED TO REMEMBER THAT.
YOU NEED TO KEEP THAT
IN YOUR MINDSET.
THAT'S YOUR PERCEPTION,
ANY TIME SOMEBODY OF MY COLOR
GETS UP IN ONE OF YOUR FACES,
THEN YOU FEEL LIKE I'M
A LUNATIC. I'M CRAZY.
>> HE JUST BROUGHT IN
THE RACE CARD.
>> DID HE REALLY?
>> NOW YOU'RE MAKING IT
A BLACK THING?
>> YEAH, I THINK THAT'S
WHAT THIS
IS ALL ABOUT
BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
YOU'RE THE ONE RAISING THE ISSUE
CALLING ME A LUNATIC.
>> PHILLIP--
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> YOU'RE BRINGING THIS TO
A BLACK AND WHITE THING NOW?
WOW.
>> I MADE THE ARGUMENT
WE DON'T WANT TO KEEP THE RICE
OUTSIDE OF THAT CAN
AND YOU TOLD ME I'M
A BLEEP LUNATIC BECAUSE
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
AND THAT'S NOT
A RATIONAL ARGUMENT.
YOU MAKE THE DECISIONS
YOU NEED TO MAKE
AND I'LL MAKE THE DECISIONS
I NEED TO MAKE.
MANO A MANO IF WE HAVE TO.
I'M THE CHIEF
OF COUNTER-INTELLIGENCE.
WANG CHUNG KUNG FU EXPERT HERE.
>> IT'S LIKE WATCHING
DIVORCE COURT.
>> HE FEELS LIKE HE'S
BETTER THAN ME,
YOU KNOW, AND I THINK
IT HAS SOME SLIGHT
RACIAL UNDERTONES TO IT.
THEY'RE THE ONES THAT GO TO THE
NEXT LEVEL TO "YOU'RE CRAZY."
WHEN HE SAID THAT, I SAID,
"DON'T FORGET THAT.
I AM CRAZY."
>> HE WAS OVER HERE
JUST FREAKING OUT.
>> I'M LIKE A LOT OF BLACK MEN.
WE'RE PREPARED TO SELF-DESTRUCT
AT ANY MOMENT
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
TO A LOT OF BLACK MEN.
THEY DO SELF-DESTRUCT,
AND BAM, BAM, BAM, BAM!
I'M NOT LOOKING
TO DO ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
YOU DON'T START NONE,
THERE WON'T BE NONE.
BUT IF YOU START IT
I'M GOING TO FINISH IT
BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL LIKE
I'VE GOT ANYTHING TO LOSE
BECAUSE ONCE THEY GET
ON THE JURY
THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO VOTE FOR ME.
THEY'RE GOING TO ASK ME,
GET DOWN ON THEIR KNEES
AND BEG FOR THE RICE.
"PLEASE, LET ME HAVE SOME RICE,
MR. CHARLIE."
>> RALPH, RALPH,
HE WAS MAKING DECISIONS
FOR THE TRIBE
AND KEPT PUSHING THE ISSUE
AND THEN HE TOOK IT
TO BLACK AND WHITE,
LIKE WE WERE HAVING SOME
RACIAL ISSUE OR SOMETHING.
>> I JUST NOTICED
THAT EVERY SINGLE TIME
I MAKE AN ISSUE
WITH THE PEOPLE
OF THE FORMER ZAPATERA TRIBE,
SUDDENLY A GUY
WHO IS ABLE TO BECOME
A FEDERAL AGENT--
>> WHATEVER.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
>> SUDDENLY BECOMES
( BLEEP ) CRAZY.
YOU NOW CALLED ME CRAZY.
YOU ARE CRAZY.
EVERY TIME I MAKE THAT ARGUMENT,
SUDDENLY I'M CRAZY.
AND THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WITH SOME WHITE FOLKS.
THEY LIKE TO TAKE A BLACK MAN
AND MAKE THEM CRAZY
WHEN HE MAKES AN ARGUMENT
THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I'VE GOT
TO SAY ABOUT THAT?
RIGHT THERE, BUDDY.
>> NO, EVERY TIME I MAKE AN
ARGUMENT WITH ONE OF THOSE GUYS
IT'S I'M ( BLEEP ) CRAZY.
THAT'S ( BLEEP ) CRAZY.
GET OUT OF MY FACE WITH THAT.
I'M TIRED OF HEARING
THAT ( BLEEP ).
I'M TIRED OF
HEARING THAT ( BLEEP ).
EVERY TIME I MAKE AN ARGUMENT
WITH SOMEBODY AROUND HERE.
THAT ( BLEEP ) HAS TO BE CRAZY.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
I'VE NEVER BEEN TO JAIL.
I'VE NEVER BEEN ARRESTED.
BUT SUDDENLY I'M CRAZY
ON A LITTLE ISLAND
WITH A COUPLE OF DUDES
BECAUSE I'M TELLING THEM
HEY, MAN, I HAVE SOME BAD RICE.
I WANT TO PUT IT
IN A GOOD CONTAINER.
>> CRAZY, CRAZY,
PHIL BEING CRAZY PHIL,
TAKING IT TO THE "N" WORD
IS PRETTY WACKY.
IT'S DEGRADING.
IT'S NOT A CHIP.
IT'S A LOG ON HIS SHOULDER.
I'D JUST AS SOON TURN MY BACK
AND WALK AWAY FROM IT.
>> WE'RE VOTING FOR PHIL
TOMORROW.
JUST A THOUGHT.
>> HE'S A PAIN IN THE ASS.
HE'S A LOOSE CANNON.
AND A LITTLE SCARY, TOO.
SO THE QUICKER WE CAN GET HIM
OUT OF HERE,
I THINK THE WHOLE TRIBE
WOULD BE IN BETTER SHAPE.
>> ZERO SOCIAL SKILLS.
HE'S UNSTABLE, MAN.
>> YEAH.
>> SOMETHING LIKE THAT DOESN'T
LAST IN THE C.I.A.,
OR ANY
INVESTIGATION THING.
>> MAYBE THAT'S WHY
HE'S NOT WORKING FOR THEM.
>> MAYBE HE WAS DISCARDED
OR SOMETHING.
>> I DON'T MIND SO MUCH HIM
PICKING ON THE OTHER TRIBE,
BUT YOU CAN JUST SEE
THAT ONCE THEY'RE GONE,
THAT OLD PHILLIP'S
COMING BACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> UH-HUH.
>> WHAT STARTED OFF
AS A FRIENDLY LITTLE SONG
BETWEEN GRANT AND I
TURNED INTO AN EXPLOSION.
PHILLIP SOMEHOW MANAGED
TO MAKE A WAR ABOUT
WHITE RICE RACIAL.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT CAME FROM.
IT WAS UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> I WAS REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I WAS REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH HIM BRINGING UP
THE RACE CARD, TOO.
>> AND DROPPING THE "N" WORD.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, PHILLIP
WILL BE PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER ONE.
I JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHO TO MAKE
PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER TWO.
>> I'D STILL RATHER DIE
THAN KEEP HIM AROUND, THOUGH.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
ANDREA.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT
TO GIVE IT UP.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU MUST
BUILD A MULTISTAGE PUZZLE WHEEL.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS-- ON MY GO
ALL NINE OF YOU WILL RACE TO
RELEASE A PUZZLE BASE
AND THEN SOLVE A PUZZLE.
THE FIRST SIX TO FINISH
MOVE ON TO THE FINAL ROUND
WHERE YOU MUST SOLVE
A SECOND PUZZLE
TO COMPLETE THE WHEEL.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT,
WINS IMMUNITY,
IS SAFE IN THIS GAME.
LOSERS, YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SOMEBODY VOTED OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS
AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FIRST SIX MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST ROUND GOING
TO GET YOU VERY DIZZY.
ASHLEY MOVING QUICKLY.
PHILLIP VERY SLOW.
ROB FLYING AROUND HIS.
STEVE MOVING QUICKLY.
GRANT MOVING VERY FAST.
RALPH VERY SLOW.
ANDREA NOW IN THE LEAD.
YOU NEED TO PICK IT UP,
IF YOU WANT TO WIN!
ANDREA WORKING.
GRANT WORKING ON HIS.
JULIE, ROB WORKING.
RALPH A LITTLE DIZZY.
>> AAHH!
>> Jeff: NATALIE AND PHILLIP
WORKING.
THIS PUZZLE'S
GOING TO GO QUICKLY.
WHEN YOU HAVE IT
STEP BACK AND YELL!
>> GOT IT.
>> Jeff: ROB MOVING ON.
SIX PEOPLE ARE MOVING ON.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR FIVE MORE.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: JULIE HAS IT.
>> Jeff: RALPH HAS IT!
>> PHILLIP HAS IT.
>> GOD, I SUCK.
>> NOT QUITE. NOPE.
SORRY, BABY.
>> Jeff: ANDREA HAS IT!
THAT'S FOUR.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR TWO MORE.
STEVE IS MOVING ON!
ONE SPOT LEFT.
WHO'S IT GOING TO GO TO?
GRANT, NATALIE, ASHLEY,
OR PHILLIP?
>> WHY WON'T YOU GO IN THERE?
YOU WENT IN THERE BEFORE.
>> Jeff: GRANT RACING
TO GET HIS DONE.
GRANT MOVES ON.
STEVE, ROB, JULIE, ANDREA,
RALPH, AND GRANT
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO
FOR THE FINAL ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THE FIRST PERSON TO FIT ALL
THEIR PIECES WINS IMMUNITY.
YOU WILL NOT HAVE TO FORCE
THESE PIECES.
THEY WILL FIT EASILY.
STEVE GETTING A FAST MOVE ON IT.
ANDREA DOING A NICE JOB.
>> OH, MAN!
>> WHERE IS IT? WHERE IS IT?
WHERE IS IT?
>> Jeff: ROB STARTING TO GET
A LITTLE SOMETHING GOING.
ANDREA NOW IN THE LEAD.
ROB RIGHT THERE WITH HER.
GRANT MAKING A LOTE OF PROGRESS.
STEVE VERY CLOSE NOW.
ROB DOWN TO HIS LAST COUPLE
OF PIECES.
ANDREA CLOSER NOW.
DOWN TO HER LAST COUPLE
OF PIECES.
>> NO!
>> Jeff: WHOA, WHOA,
EASY, BROTHER, EASY.
>> GET IN THERE.
STEVE VERY CLOSE.
ROB STEPS AWAY.
THINKS HE HAS IT.
>> STEVE'S DONE.
>> Jeff: ROB HAS IT.
ROB WINS IMMUNITY!
>> WAY TO GO, ROB.
>> WAY TO GO, BABY!
>> ROBBIE.
>> Jeff: ROB, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
NICE WORK.
FINISHED FIRST IN EACH ROUND.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
ROB IS SAFE AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
( APPLAUSE )
>> YA!
>> Jeff: GUARANTEED AT LEAST
ONE MORE DAY IN THIS GAME.
EVERYBODY ELSE, AFTER 27 DAYS,
ONE OF YOU WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> THE CHALLENGE
WAS A CLOSE ONE FOR ME.
BUT I DROPPED THE BALL.
THERE'S THREE OF US RIGHT NOW
LEFT IN ZAPATERA.
OUR TARGET IS PHIL.
IF TWO OF THEM WOULD CHANGE
THEIR MIND AND VOTE
FOR PHIL, BAM.
IT'S THE ONLY SHOT WE GOT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DAMN, THAT'S GOOD.
>> I HAVE NEVER EATEN SO MUCH
RICE IN MY LIFE.
TONIGHT'S GOING TO BE
AN EASY VOTE.
THERE ARE JUST THREE OF US.
OLD ZAPATERA,
AND THERE ARE SIX OF THEM.
SO THE THREE OLD ZAPATERA
ARE VOTING FOR PHILLIP.
REALLY, WE ONLY NEED
TWO MORE VOTES,
OR ONE OF US OLD ZAPATERA
ARE LEAVING.
THE OMETEPE TRIBE
HAVE ENOUGH NUMBERS NOW
WHERE THEY CAN GET RID
OF SOMEBODY, SO TONIGHT
WOULD BE A GREAT NIGHT
TO GET RID OF PHILLIP.
PHILLIP'S RIGHT-- IT'S WAR.
PHILLIP IS GOING TO HAVE
TO HANG OUT
IN HIS CUTE LITTLE UNDERWEAR
FROM NOW ON.
I DON'T THINK HE'LL EVER
FIND THOSE.
>> MY SWIM TRUNKS
WERE ON THE LINE.
DID ANY OF YOU GIRLS MOVE THEM?
>> NO.
>> DID ANY OF YOU GUYS
MOVE MY SWIM TRUNKS?
>> I DIDN'T SEE THEM.
>> OKAY, THEY MUST HAVE GOT LEGS
AND WALKED AWAY
ALL ON THEIR OWN.
THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT CAN GET REAL FUN
AND EXCITING AROUND HERE.
>> EVERYBODY IN CAMP
IS OVER PHILLIP.
>> THE BOTTOM LINE IS I KNOW
MY TRUNKS WERE TAKEN.
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW,
I CAN PLAY THAT GAME.
>> PHILLIP SAYS ALL THE TIME
THAT, YOU KNOW,
HE WAS A SPECIAL AGENT
AND HE KNOWS HOW TO READ PEOPLE.
>> YOU'RE FROM
THE BIG HOUSE, RIGHT?
YOU FROM THE BIG HOUSE?
>> CRAZY PHILLIP
WHO WEARS FEATHERS
AND PINK UNDERWEAR.
HONESTLY, I CAN'T WAIT
TO GET RID OF PHILLIP.
>> I HOPE MY SHORTS
COME UP TONIGHT
BECAUSE IF THEY DON'T
COME UP TONIGHT,
IT'S GOING TO GET REAL
INTERESTING AROUND HERE.
>> I'M FEELING THREATENED.
>> I'M FEELING THREATENED TOO.
>> YOU SHOULDN'T FEEL
THREATENED BY ME.
BECAUSE I DON'T REALLY
THREATEN PEOPLE.
I JUST GO OFF LIKE THAT.
>> THAT'S KIND OF SCARY.
>> IT SHOULD BE.
YOU KEEP TELLING ME I'M CRAZY.
>> THIS AIN'T THE NFL.
IN THE NFL, THEY GOT RULES.
THEY GOT REFEREES.
>> CHECK HIM OUT.
>> PHIL MADE A TOTAL ASS
OUT OF HIMSELF,
GETTING RACIAL ABOUT RICE
AND CRAZY STUFF,
AND I WOULD REALLY THINK
WITH ANY KIND OF DIGNITY,
HE'D APOLOGIZE
FOR YOUR ASININE BEHAVIOR
BUT HE HASN'T SAID A WORD.
THE OMETEPE TRIBE
DON'T UNDERSTAND HIM, EITHER.
MAYBE SOMEBODY MIGHT SWAY
THE VOTE AND VOTE OUR WAY.
>> TONIGHT, IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO WE TARGET, REALLY.
YOU GOT RALPH, YOU GOT STEVE,
AND JULIE.
BUT, I DON'T KNOW.
I LOVE PHILLIP, BUT, I MEAN,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HIS HEAD IS.
THERE IS ROOM TO PLAY,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHERE.
ONE MAN SHOULD NOT HAVE
THIS MUCH POWER ON AN ISLAND,
BUT I'M GRATEFUL THAT I DO.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE FIRST MEMBER
OF OUR JURY, DAVID.
PHILLIP, BASED ON WHAT
YOU'RE WEARING,
I'M GUESSING YOU HAD
ANOTHER MEDITATION.
>> I ACTUALLY HAD A FORMER ZAP.
THINK IT WAS CUTE AND
STEAL MY CLOTHES.
THOUGHT IT WAS REAL FUNNY.
>> Jeff: DID YOU LOOK AT STEVE?
>> YEAH, I LOOKED AT STEVE
BECAUSE I COULD TELL
THAT HE WAS THE ONE
WHO REMOVED MY CLOTHES.
>> Jeff: AND YOU COULD TELL--
THIS GOES BACK
TO YOUR FORMER TRAINING?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I CONFRONTED STEVE
ABOUT THE FACT THAT THEY
WERE DELIBERATELY
CONSUMING ALL THE RICE.
SO IT'S BEEN WAR
BETWEEN THE TWO TRIBES.
>> Jeff: SO, STEVE,
PHILLIP IS ASSERTING
THAT THE THE FORMER
ZAPATERA ARE EATING
A LOT MORE RICE
THAN ANYBODY ELSE, TRUE?
>> WELL AS THE MOUTHS STARTED
DISAPPEARING FROM
THE ZAPATERA TRIBE,
WE DIDN'T HAVE TO RATION AS MUCH
SO WE'RE EATING OUR FOOD
THE WAY WE CHOOSE TO.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, THE ZAPATERA
TRIBE IS MAKING THE ARGUMENT
THAT IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS
HOW MUCH RICE WE EAT.
>> IT IS A LITTLE FRUSTRATING
BECAUSE WE WILL LOOK OUT AND
THEY WILL HAVE THIS BOWL FULL
OF RICE FOR THREE OF THEM.
IT JUST SUCKS
BECAUSE WE HAVE MAGGOTS
IN THE BOTTOM OF OUR CONTAINER.
>> PHILLIP WAS BRINGING THIS
INTO A WHOLE RACIAL
BLACK AND WHITE THING
ABOUT THE RICE.
>> Jeff: WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
>> I WAS RELAXED AND YOU WENT
INTO A RACIAL TIRADE
AND BRINGING THE "N" WORD UP
ABOUT YOURSELF.
>> Jeff: WHOA.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> JEFF, IT GOT UGLY.
HE STARTED THREATENING STEVE.
>> Jeff: HOW SO?
>> HE STARTED THREATENING ME
WITH TAE KWON DO
OR JUJITSU OR SOMETHING.
HE GOES, "WHEN I SNAP, I SNAP."
>> SO HE GOES YOU'RE CRAZY
AND THEN THE "N" WORD CAME OUT.
>> Jeff: WHO BROUGHT UP
THE "N" WORD?
>> PHILLIP BROUGHT UP
THE "N" WORD.
>> I'M GOING TO INTERRUPT HERE.
STEVE LIKES TO CALL ME CRAZY
WHENEVER I BRING
A RATIONAL ARGUMENT,
THIS RICE IS SPOILING,
WE CAN PUT IT ALL
IN THE SAME CAN.
WE CAN'T DO IT.
WHY NOT?
YOU'RE CRAZY, YOU'RE CRAZY,
YOU'RE CRAZY.
HE RESORTS TO CALLING ME CRAZY
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T WANT
TO SAY THE "N" WORD.
HE SAYS CRAZY, CRAZY, CRAZY.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, YOU'RE SAYING
WHEN STEVE CALLS YOU CRAZY
HE'S SAYING THE "N" WORD.
>> YOU KNOW, RICHARD PRYOR MADE
A MOST FAMOUS COMEDY ALBUM
OF ALL TIME.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE NAME OF IT IS?
"THAT 'N' IS CRAZY."
BECAUSE WE KNOW THAT SOMETIMES
WHEN WE CONFRONT
CERTAIN TYPES OF INDIVIDUALS,
THAT'S ONE WAY
THAT THEY TRY TO REPRESENT THAT.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, I'M TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE YOU'RE MAKING THAT LEAP,
THE CRAZY EQUALS THE "N" WORD
BECAUSE IT'S VERY TRICKY
WHEN YOU HAVE
A WHITE GUY AND A BLACK GUY
TALKING ABOUT RACE
AND THE "N" WORD
BECAUSE IT HAS SUCH AN UGLY
HISTORY TO IT.
>> YOU KNOW, DO YOU KNOW WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO BE A WOMAN?
>> Jeff: I DON'T.
>> RIGHT, YOU DON'T.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE AN AFRICAN AMERICAN.
>> Jeff: OKAY, PHILLIP--
>> LET ME FINISH.
YOU ASKED ME A QUESTION.
I'M GOING TO GO THERE.
WHEN I WORKED FOR THE GOVERNMENT
AS A FEDERAL AGENT IN THE
DEPARTMENT THAT WORKED IN
I WAS THE ONLY ONE OF 67.
I CAN'T SUM IT UP
FOR YOU IN WORDS,
BUT I KNOW IT WHEN I SEE IT.
JUST LIKE A WOMAN KNOWS IT WHEN
A GUY MAKES
AN INAPPROPRIATE REMARK.
SHE CAN'T PUT IT INTO WORDS BUT
SHE KNOWS SHE DOESN'T LIKE IT
AND I'VE SEEN IT MANY TIMES
IN MY LIFE,
AND THAT'S WHAT HE DOES.
>> Jeff: LET ME USE
YOUR SAME LOGIC ON YOU.
YOU'RE SAYING I'M NOT BLACK
SO I DON'T KNOW.
HOW DO YOU KNOW WHAT HE MEANS
WHEN HE SAYS "CRAZY?"
THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING
TO GET AT.
THERE'S A JUMP IN LOGIC
THAT I NEED THE GAP FILLED.
>> WHEN MY FATHER AND I MOVED TO
UPSTATE NEW YORK
HE AND I WENT
TO THE GROCERY STORE TOGETHER
AND THE MAN BEHIND THE COUNTER
SAID TO ME FATHER,
"WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU, BOY?"
"YOU TALKING TO ME?"
"YEAH, I'M TALKING TO YOU.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU, BOY?"
HE DIDN'T USE THE "N" WORD
BUT HE TOOK MY FATHER DOWN
TO A VERY LOW LEVEL.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY--
>> YOU CAN SAY WHAT YOU WANT
WHEN I'M FINISHED.
>> I PLAYED 13 YEARS IN THE NFL,
THE LAST SEVEN YEARS
WITH THE LOS ANGELES RAIDERS
WHERE ONE FIFTH
OF THE TEAM WAS WHITE.
THERE IS NO LINE OF
BLACK AND WHITE IN MY HEART.
>> Jeff: I'M STARTING
TO GET SOME CLARITY.
IF STEVE SAID, "I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S A CRAZY ARGUMENT.
IT DOESN'T REALLY MAKE
ANY SENSE TO ME."
YOU WOULD SAY, "THAT'S A GUY
SAYING HE DOESN'T LIKE
MY THOUGHT PROCESS."
BUT WHEN SOMEBODY SAYS,
"YOU'RE CRAZY"
IT'S ALMOST BRINGING UP
EVERY UGLY ASSOCIATION
YOU CAN THINK OF IN ONE WORD.
SO TELL ME IF THIS
IS RIGHT SO FAR.
THERE'S BEEN A BIG DEBATE
BREWING ABOUT LIVING TOGETHER.
IT CULMINATED WITH THE RICE,
AND YOU THREW AN IDEA OUT
THAT YOU FELT WAS REASONABLE.
STEVE SAID, "I DON'T KNOW.
LET'S FIGURE IT OUT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT."
AND THEN AS THE ARGUMENT
ABOUT THE RICE CONTINUED,
STEVE MADE A COMMENT THAT SAID,
"I DON'T LIKE IT.
YOU'RE CRAZY."
AT THAT POINT YOU EQUATED THAT
WITH YOU'RE CALLING ME
THE "N" WORD
AND NOW WE HAVE A WHOLE NEW
WORLD WE'RE DEALING WITH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: OKAY,
NOW I'M CAUGHT UP.
TWO PEOPLE FROM DIFFERENT WORLDS
HAD AN ARGUMENT.
YOU TOOK IT ONE WAY.
NOBODY CAN QUESTION
THE WAY YOU TOOK IT
AND IT'S BASED
ON YOUR EXPERIENCES
AND THOSE OF PEOPLE
BEFORE YOU.
NOBODY KNOWS STEVE'S INTENTIONS,
OTHER THAN STEVE RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE NOBODY HERE
REALLY KNOWS STEVE.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY BACKGROUND
ON STEVE.
IT'S QUITE POSSIBLE BOTH OF YOU
ARE TELLING THE TRUTH.
THAT THAT FELT VERY MUCH LIKE
THE "N" WORD
AND HE ABSOLUTELY
DIDN'T MEAN IT THAT WAY.
IS THAT A FAIR ASSESSMENT?
>> SURE.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: SO, ROB, HOW DO YOU
GO FORWARD AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHEN ALL OF THIS IS IN THE
CONTEXT OF A MILLION-DOLLAR
PRIZE?
>> NOT EASY.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT TONIGHT.
IS THIS GOING TO FACTOR IN?
I'M GUESSING MAYBE
ON SOME LEVEL,
CONSCIOUS OR SUBCONSCIOUS.
>> I MEAN, PHILLIP
IS A GROWN MAN.
HE SAYS AND FEELS WHAT HE WANTS.
STEVE IS A GROWN MAN.
I MEAN, IT'S PROBLEMATIC,
BUT IT'S REAL.
YOU HAVE PEOPLE THAT HAVE
DISAGREEMENTS ABOUT THINGS,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I CAN'T IMAGINE THIS
NOT FACTORING INTO OUR DECISION.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, HOW DOES IT
IMPACT THE GAME?
>> IT'S REALLY HARD FOR ME
TO SIT HERE AND JUST LISTEN
BECAUSE I FEEL FOR STEVE
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
THAT HE HAS ANY PREJUDICE
IN HIM.
AND THEN I FEEL FOR PHILLIP,
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE
AN AFRICAN AMERICAN MAN.
>> Jeff: OKAY. LAST QUESTION.
SHORTS-- WHERE ARE THEY?
WHO TOOK THEM?
WHO HAS THEM?
>> I TOOK THE SHORTS!
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
>> NOBODY WILL EVER FIND THEM.
I DUG A HOLE AND BURIED THEM
AND A ROCK ON TOP OF THEM.
>> Jeff: IF THIS WERE THERAPY
I WOULD SAY VERY GOOD SESSION.
WE'LL COME BACK WEDNESDAY
AND DO IT AGAIN.
JULIE, IF YOU'RE
A ZAPATERA MEMBER
YOU'RE HOPING FOR A CRACK
IN THE OMETEPE.
MAYBE YOU JUST FOUND IT.
>> YEAH, HOPEFULLY
THEY'RE SEEING
THAT WE WOULD BE A HAPPY FAMILY
IF THERE JUST WASN'T
THIS ONE DIVISION.
>> Jeff: STEVE, CLEARLY,
YOU'RE UNCOMFORTABLE
BEING LABELED AS A RACIST.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: BUT IN A GAME
FOR A MILLION DOLLARS
WOULD YOU BE FINE
IF AS A RESULT
OF THIS ARGUMENT
YOU WERE A PART OF,
PHILLIP GETS VOTED OUT?
>> I WOULD BE HAPPY
BUT NOT CONCERNING
ANY BLACK AND WHITE ISSUE.
WE HAVE THREE VOTES GOING
THAT WAY,
AND HOPING ONE OR TWO OTHERS
MIGHT BE GETTING TIRED
OF HIM AS WE ARE.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, IF YOU ARE
VOTED OUT TONIGHT
AT THIS MOMENT,
DO YOU BELIEVE IT WOULD
BE BASED ON ANYTHING RACIAL?
>> IF FOR SOME REASON TONIGHT
THEY FELT LIKE
OH, WE NEED TO LET PHILLIP GO
AT THIS POINT IN TIME,
THEN THAT'S THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: WELL, THIS HAS
DEFINITELY BEEN
A FASCINATING TRIBAL COUNCIL
BECAUSE IT ILLUSTRATES
HOW YOU LIVE TOGETHER
IN A SOCIETY
AND GET ALONG IN A GAME
IN WHICH YOU
THEN HAVE TO VOTE PEOPLE OUT,
SEND THEM TO A JURY,
AND GET THEM TO VOTE FOR YOU
FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS.
YOU ARE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER
FROM THIS POINT FORWARD.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CANNOT VOTE FOR ROB.
HE HAS THE NECKLACE.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
STEVE, YOU'RE UP.
>> I HOPE YOU FIND PEACE
IN YOUR HEART SOME DAY, BROTHER.
THERE'S NO PREJUDICE INVOLVED
WITH THE CRAZY COMMENT.
>> IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE COLOR
OF YOUR SKIN, PHIL.
YOU ARE ONE CRAZY DUDE.
>> PHILLIP, I HOPE YOU HAVE
A GREAT NIGHT
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND
WITH THE UNDERWEAR
AND YOUR TWO FEATHERS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY
THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT
WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, PHILLIP.
PHILLIP.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP.
THREE VOTES PHILLIP.
JULIE.
ONE VOTE JULIE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES JULIE.
JULIE. WE'RE TIED,
THREE VOTES PHILLIP,
THREE VOTES JULIE.
JULIE.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JULIE.
THREE VOTES PHILLIP.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND,"
JULIE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
>> I GUESS YOU'RE NEVER
GOING TO FIND YOUR SHORTS.
>> Jeff: YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
JULIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND,
GOOD LUCK.
WELL, TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL
IS INDICATIVE
OF HOW THIS GAME
IS GOING TO GO
FROM THIS POINT FORWARD.
EVERYTHING YOU SAY,
EVERYTHING YOU DO
MAY HAVE A DIRECT IMPACT
ON WHETHER OR NOT
YOU GET A SHOT AT WINNING
THE MILLION DOLLARS.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR
SCENES FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR.
>> I'M TRULY BLESSED.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP HAS HIS
GREATEST DAY YET.
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT GETTING RID
OF THE RIGHT PERSON
AT THE RIGHT TIME.
>> Jeff: WHILE ANDREA COULD BE
SCHEDULED FOR AN EARLY
DEPARTURE.
>> I'M JUST SO OVER
THIS GAME, MAN.
>> Jeff: AND MATT PLUMBS TO
THE DARKEST DEPTHS
OF HIS SOUL.
>> I'M OUT HERE WASTING AWAY.
GOD HAS LITERALLY
BEEN CARRYING ME.
>> HERE I AM AT REDEMPTION.
I WAS NOT EXPECTING THIS.
I REALLY THOUGHT IT WAS
GOING TO BE STEVE OR RALPH.
BUT I'M OKAY WITH IT.
IT JUST WAS AN UGLY TRIBAL.
THERE'S POISON IN THAT TRIBE,
AND HIS NAME IS PHILLIP.
AND IT'S KIND OF NICE
TO BE REMOVED FROM IT.
AARRGGHHH! DID I SCARE YOU GUYS?