Jeff: TONIGHT, GET READY TO
TAKE A CLOSER LOOK AT 19 NEW
SCENES FROM ONE OF THE MOST
MEMORABLE SEASONS OF "SURVIVOR."
THIS GAME HAS BROUGHT NEW
MEANING TO LEADERSHIP, HUMILITY,
WINNING, AND LOSING.
THIS IS THE FIRST 27 DAYS OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC."
WITH SOME OF THE MOST MEMORABLE
FIRST-TIME PLAYERS IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY, TWO LEGENDARY FORMER
PLAYERS RETURN TO THE GAME FOR A
SHOT AT REDEMPTION.
BOTH WERE QUICK TO SET UP THEIR
CORE ALLIANCES.
I'VE GOT A SOLID ALLIANCE
WITH RICK, SOPHIE, BRANDON,
EDNA, AND ALBERT.
MY FIVE-PERSON ALLIANCE RIGHT
NOW IS MYSELF, KEITH, WHITNEY,
ELYSE, AND JIM.
Jeff: THEY LED TWO OF THE
MOST EVENLY MATCHED TRIBES EVER.
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY!
SAVAII WINS IMMUNITY!
BUT COACH STRUGGLED TO CONTROL
AN UNRULY ALLY.
I KIND OF TOLD YOU GUYS TO
VOTE FOR MIKAYLA.
YOU SEE THE LIE, HOW THE LIE
CAME OUT.
STOP IT.
I'M TELLING YOU.
NO, I WANT YOU TO STOP IT.
Jeff: AND COCHRAN WAS LEFT
DODGING BULLETS ALL ALONG THE
WAY.
WHY?
PHYSICALLY HE'S GOING TO BE A
THREAT TO HIMSELF.
I HATE TO SAY IT, COCHRAN,
BUT YOU LOST IT FOR US.
Jeff: AFTER THE MERGE, BOTH
TRIBES WERE SIX STRONG.
CHEERS, EVERYBODY.
Jeff: AND COACH FOUND A
CHIRCHG IN THE ARMOR OF THE
FORMER SAVAII.
THERE'S A LINE IN THE SAND.
Jeff: AND AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, COCHRAN DID CROSS THAT
LINE.
AND KEITH WAS VOTED OUT, FOLLOW
BY OZZY.
I WILL BE BACK.
I HOPE TO SEE ALL OF YOU COMING
THROUGH REDEMPTION, AND I'LL
SEND YOU ON YOUR WAY.
Jeff: OZZY WAS EXILED TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
LEAVING COACH IN FULL CONTROL OF
THE GAME.
I'M OUT HERE TO WIN.
I'M ON THE HERE TO GO STEP BY
STEP AND BE THE LAST MAN
STANDING.
Jeff: TONIGHT, WE'LL SEE
NEW SCENES.
I'M READY TO BE SEDUCED.
SEDUCE HER!
Jeff: UNCOVER-UP HIDDEN
STRATEGIES.
MIXING THINGS UP THIS EARLY
CRAZY.
Jeff: REVEAL PREVIOUSLY
UNTOLD STORIES.
I WOULD SCREW MY TRIBE OVER.
YOU HAVE MY WORD THAT ME AND YOU
TO THE END.
Jeff: AND GIVE NEW INSIGHT
INTO THE ONGOING ADVENTURE OF
"SURVIVOR."
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Jeff: IN THE EARLY DAYS OF
THE GAME, THE TWO TRIBES TOOK
DIFFERENT APPROACHES TO CAMP
LIFE.
GET EVERYTHING FIGURED OUT
AND WORK ON THE SHELTER.
Reporter:
Jeff: THESE DIFFERENCES
DEFINED THEIR JOURNEY.
WE'LL PUT ONE HERE AND ONE
HERE.
LET'S DO IT.
Jeff: THROUGH THE REST OF
THE GAME.
AT STAVIE--
YOU GUYS WANT TO GO SWIMMING?
Jeff: OZZY LED A CARE-FREE
TRIBE WITH A LAID BACK ATTITUDE
BUT COCHRAN AND DAWN HAD TROUBLE
GETTING ON THE PARTY TRAIN.
MAN, THAT HURTS.
WE'RE ON A TROPICAL ISLAND BUT
WE ARE A TON MORE MODEST I THINK
THE WAY WE DRESS DAY TO DAY.
YOU GUYS COMING OR NOT?
NOT HAVING THE SWIM SEE THE
SUITIS A LITTLE BIT OF A DILEMMA
FOR ME BECAUSE I'M NOT USED TO
SWIMMING WITH PEOPLE I JUST MET.
IN THE NUDE.
IN MY UNDERWEAR.
I HAVE SIX KIDS.
COME ON, GUYS.
COME ON, MOM!
THIS IS LIKE THE EQUIVALENT
OF ASKING ME TO, LIKE, BE-- AM I
BY MYSELF HERE?
OH, JUST DO IT!
I DON'T SEE HIM GOING IN, IN
HIS UNDERWEAR.
NO ONE IS GIVING HIM A HARD
TIME.
I WAS VERY, VERY NERVOUS TO
STRIP DOWN TO MY UNDERWEAR AND
JUST WALTZ INTO THE WATER.
I'M NOT IN HORRIBLE PHYSICAL
CONDITION.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS THE WEST SHAPE
I'VE EVER BEEN IN.
AS PATHETIC AS IT IS TO SAY,
THIS IS AS GOOD AS IT GETS FOR
ME.
OH, NO.
YOU WORK IN LAS VEGAS.
THIS IS NORMAL FUR.
WORK WITH ME!
RIP IT OFF N-
NO!
WHAT HAS HAPPENED TO THE
YOUTH OF THIS GENERATION.
GET YOUR BUTT IN HERE!
COME ON!
THIS IS SO PAINFUL.
I'M FROM SALT LAKE CITY, HELLO!
YOU GUYS ARE LUCKY I'M NOT IN A
TURTLENECK.
Jeff: COCHRAN'S BODY ISSUES
WERE THE FIRST OF MANY
PERSONALITY QUIRKS THAT WOULD
KEEP HIM FROM FITTING IN.
THE GUYS, MYSELF EXCLUDED,
HAVE GONE OUT FISHING, AND THE
LADIES, MYSELF INCLUDED, HAVE
BEEN TENDING TO THE CAMP.
WE'VE GOT 10.
>>
( CHEERS )
MY GOD!
OH, IT'S GOING TO BE THE BEST
DAY EVER!
WHO WANTS TO GUT?
EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT THE
STRONGEST GUY ON THE TRIBE THERE
IS SOME SORT OF CAVE MAN IN ME
THAT'S JUST WAITING TO BREAK
OUT.
OH, COCHRAN, YOU BETTER BE
CAREFUL.
YOU'VE GOT ME SCARED.
TURN THE MACHETE THE OTHER WAY.
HE LOVES THIS.
HE LIVES FOR THIS.
I'M WATCHING AND LEARNING.
PLEASE, DON'T CUT YOUR HANDS.
TURNS OUT IN ORDER TO EAT THE
FISH, YOU FIRST HAVE TO TEAR
OPEN ITS UNDERSIDE AND PULL OUT
ALL THE UNDEDESIRABLE ORGANS AND
WHATEVER THE SLIME IS I'M
PULLING OUT OF THE FISH WHICH IS
OUT OF MY COMFORT ZONE.
BACK AT HOME I'M A BIG FAN OF
ANIMALS.
I'M A ANIMAL LOVER.
I'M ALL ABOUT RESPECTING ANIMAL
AND I FEEL LIKE THE FISH RESPECT
ME.
THEY UNDERSTAND ME.
THEY KNOW WHEN I'M GUTTING THEM
I'M VERY RESPECTFUL ABOUT IT.
I DON'T PUT FINGERS ANYWHERE I
WOULD NOT WANT FINGERS PUT IN MY
BODY.
I WAS WILLING TO DO IT, ALTHOUGH
I HOPE TO NEVER HAVE TO DO IT
AGAIN.
Jeff: AT UPOLU--
LOOKING BEAUTIFUL.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU.
Jeff: COACH WAS NOT ONLY
BUILDING A STRONGER FOUNDATION--
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW LUCKY IT
IS TO HAVE A BUNCH OF WORKERS.
Jeff: HE WAS BUILDING A
FAMILY.
IT'S A LOT OF FUN TO COME OUT
HERE AND PLAY IN GAME WITH
PEOPLE WHO CARE ABOUT CAMP LIFE,
PEOPLE THAT CARE ABOUT BUILDING
A SHELTER AND THIRD TIME AROUND,
COACH HAS FINALLY GOT THE
LEADERSHIP ROLE.
I APPRECIATE THE ADVICE.
CHECKING UP ON EVERYBODY.
YOU RAKING?
YOU GOT TO.
IT SNEAKS UP-- YOU OUT HERE.
I'M GOING TO DO WHAT COACH
SAYS.
I KNOW THAT THE SAVAII CAMP,
THEY ALREADY HAVE FOOD.
OZZY'S GREAT AT CATCHING FISH.
HE IS THE GREAT TYPE OF SURVIVOR
TO HAVE OUT HERE NEXT TO YOU.
AND I'LL JUST TELL YOU RIGHT
NOW, JUST BEING FLATONT, IF I
WAS OUT HERE WOULD I RATHER HAVE
COACH WADE ON MY TRIBE OR OZZY?
I'D RATHER HAVE OZZY ON MY
TRIBE.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M NOT A GREAT SURVIVOR.
BUT THE PERCEPTION IN OUR TRIBE
RIGHT NOW IS WE HAVE IT GOING
ON.
GO CRAZY ON IT.
I'M VERY, VERY GLAD.
I'M GRAD COACH IS HERE.
WHEN JEFF TOLD US AS AS A GROUP
THERE WERE GOING TO BE TWO
PEOPLE JOINING US I WAS HOPING
FOR COACH BECAUSE COACH HAS
PLAYED LOYAL TRICE, AND YOU GOT
TO TRUST THE GUY.
I MEAN, IT MAY BE A MISTAKE FOR
ME TRUSTING HIM, BUT I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT, I'M WILLING TO TAKE
THAT CHANCE.
I CAN GET A COMMITMENT FROM
YOU, COACH?
JUST TAKE ME AS FAR AS YOU CAN.
HOW ABOUT IF I SAY THE SAME
THING TO YOU.
ABSOLUTELY.
HEY, MAN, IF YOU'RE GOING TO
BE A MAN OF YOUR WORD, I'M
DESPERATE TO PLAY WITH PEOPLE
LIKE THAT.
PLEASE DO.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT CHANGING JUST
BECAUSE YOU'RE PLAYING THE THIRD
TIME.
DUDE, I'M TELLING YOU THE
THIRD TIME STRAIGHT UP AS A MAN
OF JOB, I CAN'T CHANGE.
I HAVE MAD RESPECT FOR COACH.
WE CAN CHANGE THE COURSE OF THIS
GAME.
WE CAN MAKE IT A MORE AROUNDABLE
NOBODY WOULD HAVE GUESSED THAT
RUSSELL HANTZ'S NEPHEW WOULD DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT AND THAT'S
WHAT I WANT TO BE KNOWN AS.
I WANT TO BE KNOWN AS AN HONEST
PLAYER.
IF THAT WILL BE MY DEMISE SO BE
IT.
DO YOU GIVE ME YOUR WORD?
AS A MAN OF GOD I GIVE YOU MY
WORD.
I GIVE YOU MY WORD AS A MAN
OF GOD.
Jeff: RUSSELL HANTZ WAS
NOTORIOUS FOR SABOTAGING CAMP,
BUT HIS NEPHEW, BRANDON HANTZ,
SOUGHT REDEMPTION OF THE FAMILY
NAME BY BECOMING A PROVIDER.
YOU GOING FISHING?
YES, SIR.
WOKE UP THIS MORNING EARLY, FELT
GOOD, DECIDED TO TAKE THE BOAT
OUT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
YOU ALL STAY ON THE RIGHT SIDE.
I WANTED TO KIND OF BUTTER UP MY
TRIBE A LITTLE BIT, SEE WHAT I
COULD DO.
BRANDON'S GOING TO BE THE NEW
OZZY.
NEVER, EVER, EVER DONE SPEAR
FISHING BEFORE IN MY LIFE.
IT'S FUN.
IT'S DANGEROUS BECAUSE OF THE
CORAL AND THE WAVES.
OZZY WHO?
AND I LIKE IT.
Jeff: ALTHOUGH HE TRIED TO
HIDE HIS TRUE IDENTITY, SOVY HAD
HER SUSPICIONS ABOUT HIM.
BRANDON IS SO GOOD AT
FISHING, HE SO GOOD AT
PROVIDING, BUT I FEEL LIKE HE'S
HIDING SOMETHING.
HE'S COVERING ALL THESE TATTOOS.
REALLY CREEPY.
HE COULD BE SOME, LIKE,
REFORMED,UN, EX-GANGSTER READY
TO PRAISE GOD FOR 39 DAYS.
SO I JUST NEED TO KEEP MY EYE ON
HIM.
Jeff: COMING UP NEXT.
PAPA BEAR IS A NUT, GIVING ME
GIRL ADVICE.
I'M READY TO BE SEDUCED.
PORK BATH READY.
OH, MY STOMACH.
ARE YOU GUYS REALLY EATING
THAT?
MIKAYLA IS SICK, BUT I DON'T
CARE.
SHE'S GOING HOME NEXT.
♪ ♪ ♪
YOU ACTUALLY WANT TO GO TO
LAW SCHOOL?
I DO.
Jeff: COCHRAN WASN'T A
PHYSICAL THREAT IN CHALLENGES OR
A PROVIDER TO HIS TRIBE SO HE
HAD TO DEPEND ON HIS SOCIAL GAME
TO INTEGRATE HIMSELF WITHIN
SAVAII.
NOW THAT THE SHADE HAS MOVED
AWAY I HAVE TO INCH FEBRUARY
FURTHER AWAY LIKE A HERMIT CRAB
SIDEWAYS.
COCHRAN IS LIKE A KID IN A
MAN'S BODY.
HE LOOKS LIKE A SHELTERED KID.
HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S AFRAID TO DO
THINGS.
I LIKE HIM.
I REALLY DO LIKE HIM.
WE ALL LIKE HIM.
HE HAS A GOOD HEART.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE I WANT TO
FATHER HIM BECAUSE I THINK THIS
EXPERIENCE WILL BE A GOOD THING
FOR HIM.
ELYSE, SHE'S BEAUTIFUL AND
SMART.
IF YOU WERE IN A BAR, YOU WOULD
LIKE HER, WOULDN'T YOU?
YEAH.
I'D BE INTIMIDATED, PROBABLY.
YOU LIKE SOMEBODY, YOU GO UP
TO THEM-- THIS IS WHAT I WANT
YOU TO DO.
IT'S NOT THAT DIFFERENT FROM A
GUY.
YOU WALK OVER.
THIS IS WHAT--
I DO THAT WITH MY HANDS, KIND
OF SLOWLY.
YOU WEAR A TIGHT SHIRT.
A TIGHT SHIRT ON TOP, MUSCLES
POPPING OUT.
THIS IS ALREADY A BAD IDEA.
YOU'VE GOT TO DO THIS.
THEN YOU WALK OVER, AND YOU SAY,
"HI, HOW YOU DOING?
CAN I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
I REALLY LIKE THOSE EARRINGS."
REVERSE IT.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S GOING TO
WORK AT ALL FOR ME "I REALLY
LIKE THOSE EARRINGS."
PAMMA BEAR IS A NUT GIVING ME
GIRL ADVICE.
I'LL TAKE IT BUT I DON'T
PARTICULARLY WANT IT.
LIKE MY COCONUT EARRINGS?
OH, YEAH, DID YOU SEE THE
PICKUP ADVICE THAT PAPA BEAR
GAVE ME.
THE WHAT?
HOW TO PICK UP GIRLS?
HOW.
I'LL DO-- I'LL DO THE ACT.
PLEASE.
I'LL TELL YOU IF IT WOULD WORK
ON ME, OKAY.
VERY, VERY SHORT.
YOU'RE AT THE BAR.
OKAY.
I SPOT YOU--
I'M AT THE COCONUT BAR.
I SPOT YOU ACROSS THE ROOM
AND I LIKE WHAT I SEE.
SO I START WIPING MY HANDS LIKE
THIS IN A VERY SEDUCTIVE WAY.
DO IT SLOWER.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
YEAH.
I LIKED IT.
I'M READY TO BE SEDUCED.
SEDUCE HER!
SEE, IT DOESN'T WORK.
IT WILL WORK.
I SAW YOU AT THIS STORE
ACROSS THE STREET AND I NOTICED
THE EARRINGS YOU WERE WEARING.
I WAS GOING TO GET THEM FOR MY
SISTER OR SOMETHING, SO WHERE
DID YOU GET THOSE EAR?
AND I GUESS I PIVOT--
NO, YOU IDIOT.
THEN YOU SAY SOMETHING LIKE,
"WHY WHEREDID YOU GET THEM?"
SOFT EYE CONTACT.
SOFT, GOOD, GOOD.
I'M MELTING INTO YOU.
AND YOU SAY, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE A VERY PRETTY GIRL."
OH, YEAH, I CAN'T DO THAT.
YEAH, THAT'S TOO MUCH.
I'M TELLING YOU, AS A GIRL.
HELP HER.
DON'T SAY, THAT EVER.
THE EARRINGS, HONESTLY, IF YOU
CAME UP AND TOLD ME THAT YOU
THOUGHT MY EARRINGS WERE GOOD I
WOULD THINK YOU WERE GAY.
Jeff: IF GETTING SHOT DOWN
WASN'T BAD ENOUGH, AT THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE-- GO!
COCHRAN AND THE REST OF SAVAII--
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
MISSED OUT ON PORK IN THEIR
BELLY.
IN ADDITION YOU CAN TAKE HOME
ALL THE MEAT YOU COLLECTED.
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT, BABY!
Jeff: COACH WAS A KIND AND
BENEVOLENT FATHER TO HIS FAMILY,
BUT NOT SO MUCH TO OUTSIDERS, AS
MIKAYLA QUICKLY LEARNED WHEN SHE
COMMITTED THE HAINOS SIN OF
OVERCOOPING HER MORNING COFFEE.
MY SYSTEM.
A MESS, MAN.
BECAUSE OF THE PORK.
IT WAS THE LAST GREASY ONES
WE MADE.
I WENT TO BED AND IT WAS SITTING
HERE AND I GOT IT UP.
THREW YOU UP?
OH, YEAH.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE PORK TODAY.
I DON'T WANT TO TOUCH IT IT.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO GO NEAR IT.
YOU FREAKING KIDDING ME?
JUST LET ME VENT FOR A LITTLE
BIT, OKAY?
I'M WATCHING MIKAYLA, YOU KNOW.
THE GIRL, YOU KNOW, HAD TWO
HEAPING TEA SPOONS OF SUGAR AND
I KNOW BECAUSE I'VE BEEN OUT
HERE WITH NOTHING.
YOU GUYS HAVE NOT BEEN OUT HERE
WITH NOTHING SO WHEN I SEE HER
WITHOUT ASKING ANYONE Q.B. PUT
TWO HEAPING TEA SPOONS IN HER
COFFEE THAT BOTHERS ME MAN.
I KNOW I'M CRAZY.
I'M VENTING SO I DON'T SAY
ANYTHING TO THE TRIBE.
MIKAYLA IS A PROBLEM.
THIS MORNING, I FIXED EIGHT CUPS
OF COFFEE.
I USED ONE TEASPOON OF CREAM AND
SUGAR KIND.
AND MIKAYLA, SHE HAD ONE COUPLE
OF COFFEE AND SHE PUT IN TWO
SCOOPS OF CREAM AND SUGGAAAR.
SHE'S SELFISH AND I WAS AND
TIRED OF WATCHING IT.
I'M THINKING OF TAKING SOME
OF THAT FAT AND PUT IT OVER
THIFY.
YOU WANT TO EAT LARD?
I WANT TO GET A COUPLE PIECES
IN MY BELLY.
IT SMELLS RANK.
KEEP THOSE FLAMES GOING, MAN.
I WANT TO ROAST THE FAT.
OH, MY STOMACH.
PORK FAT'S READY.
DID YOU EAT THAT?
ARE YOU GUYS REALLY EATING
THAT?
THERE'S A LITTLE BIT OF BILE
COMING UP INTO MY THROAT.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU ARE SUCH AN ASS.
I ATE PURE PIG FAT.
MAYBE THAT WAS INSENSITIVE OF
ME, BUT I DON'T CARE.
MIKAYLA IS WEAK RIGHT NOW.
SHE'S SICK.
BESIDES, SHE'S GOING HOME NEXT.
OUCH.
Jeff: WHILE COACH WAS
MAKING MIKAYLA'S STOMACH TURN,
COCHRAN WAS BUSY MAKING HIS OWN
TRIBE CRINGE.
GENTLE ROCKING?
IF YOU WANT TO PUSH, I'M NOT
GOING TO STOP YOU.
TELL ME A STORY.
UH, I'M TRYING TO THINK.
I CAN TELL YOU A KIND OF
DISGUSTING KINDERGARTEN STORY.
OH, GOOD.
I'M READY.
SO I WAS IN KINDERGARTEN, AND
IT WAS NAP TIME AND I KNEW
FIWENT TO THE BATHROOM DURING
NAP TIME EVERYBODY WOULD HEAR
EVERYTHING I'M DOING IN THE
BATHROOM.
RIGHT.
SO I DECIDED I'D GO IN MY
PANTS.
LIKE IN HUGGIES OR JUST
PANTS?
NO UNDERWEAR AND LITTLE
KHAKIS.
LIKE I AM NOW.
BASICALLY LIKE I AM NOW BUT
THREE FEET TALL.
COCHRAN'S STORIES, THEY COULD
MAKE THE WORLD GO ROUND, I'M
PRETTY SURE.
COCHRAN TOLD THIS STORY ABOUT
KINDERGARTEN AND A POET
ACCIDENT.
I WAS PROBABLY CRYING OR
SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, YEAH.
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT LOVE THE GUY.
WHAT A WEIRD KID.
THE NAP TIME ENDED, SO I GOT
UP WITH EVERYTHING IN MY PANTS,
AND SAT DOWN IN MY SEAT, AND
EVERYTHING SQUISHED ALL AROUND.
OH!
IN MY LEGS AND EVERY CREVICE
OF MY BODY AND I GUESS THE
TEACHER GOT WISE AND SHE STARTED
GOING AROUND THE ROOM SNIFFING
EACH OF OUR BUTTS.
YEAH.
AND SHE GOT TO MY BUTT, AND OF
COURSE THAT'S JACK POT.
YOU POOR THING!
NOW THAT I'M IN THIS GAME, I
DO LIKE TO THINK I HAVE CHANGED
FROM BEING THAT FIVE-YEAR-OLD
AND THAT THAT WAS A TEACHABLE
AND LEARNABLE MOMENT IN IT MY
LIFE THAT I CAN LOOK BACK ON
FONDLY.
I AM REALIZING THE FIVE-YEAR-OLD
HAD NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.
I'M GOING TO BATHROOM IN OTHER
PLACES NOW.
Jeff: WHEN UPOLU WENT TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL--
HALF OF US ARE ON ONE SIDE,
HALF OF US ARE ON THE OTHER.
THAT'S NOT LOYALTY.
Jeff: BRANDON LAUNCHED INTO
AN IRRATIONAL OUTBURST.
VOTE ME OUT TODAY IF WE'RE
GOING TO PLAY DISLOYAL.
Jeff: BUT UNLIKE MIKAYLA,
HE WAS PART OF THE FAMILY, SO HE
WAS FORGIVEN BY COACH.
SO I WANTED TO ASK YOU, WHAT
DID YOU THINK ABOUT TRIBAL LAST
NIGHT?
WHAT DITHINK WITH TRIBAL?
UH-HUH.
I THOUGHT IT WAS UGLY.
YOU KNOW.
YEAH.
HE'S GOTTA QUIT HAVING
MELTDOWNS OR WE'RE GOING TO BE
IN TROUBLE.
DO YOU THINK IT'S GOING TO BE
A PROBLEM ONCE WE GET TO THE
MERGE?
YEAH.
BRANDON, IF HE HAS ANOTHER
MELTED DOWN WE HAVE TO GET RID
OF HIM.
WE CAN'T GET TO THE MERGE AND
START HAVING A MELTDOWN AND
TELLING HIM THE GAME PLAN AND HE
DOES EVERY TIME.
BRANDON CAN'T PLAY THIS GAME.
THE WORLD IS VERY BLACK AND
WHITE TO HIM, NOT SHADES OF
GRAY, WHICH IN REALITY IT IS.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE WAS DESIGNED
FOR THIS, IN THIS PHASE OF HIS
LIFE.
I KNOW THAT HE'S NOT BUT HE'S
HONEST AND YOU CAN USE THAT.
BUT IT'S LIKE THE THIRD TIME.
HE'LL BE FINE.
I'LL KEEP HIM UNDER CONTROL.
BRANDON HAS HAD THREE
MELTDOWNS IN TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND
TWO TIMES IT'S JUST RANDOM.
THREE TIMES, THAT'S A PATTERN.
AFTER A MERGE, WHAT'S THE
LIKELIHOOD OF HIM HAVING ANOTHER
MELTDOWN THE FOURTH TIME?
I DON'T THINK HE CAN HANDLE THE
PRESSURE OF TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHATEVER HAPPENS WE HAVE TO
KEEP STRATEGY TALK WITH BRENDAN
TO A MINIMUM.
HE CAN'T HANDLE A BIG, EXTENDED,
ANALYTICAL DEBATE.
LIKE WHAT WE DO WHEN WE SCENARIO
MAP.
IF THIS SCENARIO HAPPENS WE DO
THIS.
BRANDON'S ERUPTION AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL LAST NIGHT CONFIRMED TO
A LOT OF PEOPLE NAHE REALLY
DISTRIBUTE HAVE ANY BUSINESS IN
THIS GAME.
BRANDON IS HONEST.
BRANDON IS LOYAL.
TO A FAULT.
I MEAN, THAT'S THE THING.
BUT YOU KNOW I REALLY HAVE TO
HOPE THEY CAN CHANNEL THE
HONESTY INTO THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
SIT DOWN JUST FOR A SECOND MAN,
BECAUSE I'LL JUST TELL YOU THIS,
RIGHT.
EVERYBODY FREAKING LOVES YOU,
MAN.
THEY REALLY DO, MAN.
THEY ARE JUST CONCERNED THAT IN
A MOMENT OF BLACK AND WHITE
HONESTY, YOU'RE GOING TO JUST
SAY, "HERE'S WHAT'S GOING ON."
PRAY WITH ME, MAN.
EVERY DAY IS A STRUGGLE FOR ME.
I KNOW.
LORD, I FEEL SO STRONGLY AND I
HAVE SO MUCH FAITH THAT YOU'RE
SMILING DOWN ON US NOW, FATHER,
SO I ASK FOR A SPIRIT OF PEACE
FOR BRANDON.
GIVE HIM UNBELIEVABLE
SELF-CONTROL WHEN IT COMES TO
HIS TONGUE.
90% OF BRANDON IS RUSSELL IN HIS
STUBBORNNESS.
RUSSELL JUST WANTED TO BE
STUBBORN TO PLAY THE GAME
EVILLY.
BRANDON IS STUBBORN TO PLAY THE
GAME WITH GOOD.
BUT THE DEMONS INSIDE OF HIM
WILL HAVE TO BE WRESTLED IN
ORDER FOR HIM TO JUST BE AT
PEACE, LET ALONE SURVIVE IN
"SURVIVOR."
Jeff: COMING UP NEXT--
I'VE HAD THE DISTINCT
PLEASURE OF SLEEPING IN THE
LOVER'S BUNGALOW WITH KEITH AND
WHITNEY.
THANKS, COCHRAN.
IF THERE'S A DOUBLE HEADED
MONSTER PROWLING THE CAMP, THE
NAME IS KEITH AND WHITNEY.
WHO IS THE MOST POWERFUL MAN
ON EARTH?
HERCULES.
I'M HERCULES?
I'M FEARING COACH MAY AT SOME
POINT DEVOUR ME.
ARE YOU THE MOST POWERFUL MAN
IN THE GAME.
I LIKE THAT.
Jeff: AT SAVAII, COCHRAN
WAS BECOMING MORE AND MORE OF AN
OUTSIDER.
ALL HE COULD DO WAS WATCH FROM
THE SIDELINESSES AS THE OTHERS
GOT CLOSER AND CLOSER.
WHY, THANK YOU.
Jeff: KEITH AND WHITNEY GOT
SO CLOSE THEY TREATED CAMP LIFE
LIKE A HONEYMOON.
I REALLY DO, I LIKE WHO HE IS
AS A PERSON BUT COUPLES CAN BE
DANGEROUS IN THIS GAME.
SO YOU HAVE TO MAKE AN EFFORT
NOT TO SEEM TOO CLOSE.
WAY TO GO, WAY TO GO.
OH, GOD.
SPREAD IT OUT.
SO NONE OF THEM KNOWS WE'RE
ALIGNED.
I AGREE.
KEITH AND WHITNEY'S
RELATIONSHIP IS KIND OF A
PANDORA'S BOX FOR ME.
ON THE ONE HAND, I REALLY,
REALLY LIKE BOTH OF THEM BUT
THEIR SUPER CLOSE RELATIONSHIP
IS SOMETHING I HOPE OTHER PEOPLE
ARE NOTICING.
I WONDER THE SLEEPING
ARRANGEMENTS STUFF, BUT I DON'T
THINK THAT REALLY MATTERS AND I
DO NOT WANT TO, LIKE, SNUGGLE UP
TO COCHRAN.
( LAUGHING )
GETTING ON YOUR NERVES A LITTLE?
I'VE HAD THE DISTINCT
PLEASURE OF SLEEPING IN THE
LOVER'S BUNGALOW WITH KEITH AND
WHITNEY FOR TWO NIGHTS.
IT'S AWKWARD ON SEVERAL LEVELS.
THEY'RE JUST WISPERING AND
GIGGLING THE ENTIRE NIGHT.
THEY COMPLETELY TAKE THE ENTIRE
BLANKET FOR THEMSELVES.
I'M FREEZING MY ASS OFF.
THANKS COCHRAN!
AND THEY COMPLAIN IF I MOVE
THE SLYEST INCH DURING THE
NIGHT.
THEY ACT LIKE I'VE CREATED A
HOOSH SIN.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT WAS GOING ON
WITH KEITH AND WHITNEY IN THE
BUNGALOW.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF NINE MONTHS
FROM NOW WE'LL DISCOVER THE
PRODUCT OF THIS RELATIONSHIP.
I FEEL LIKE WE NEED TO KILL
HIM SOON.
SORRY.
Jeff: TO ADD INSULT TO
INJURY--
HERE, COCHRAN.
Jeff: OZZY WENT OUT OF HIS
WAY TO PUT COCHRAN IN
UNCOMFORTABLE SITUATIONS, MAKING
HIM THE OBJECT OF RIDICULE.
IS BLOOD GOING TO SPURT OUT.
YES.
HOLD IT DOWN.
HOLD IT CLOSE TO THE BOTTOM.
OH, GOD.
ARE YOU GOING TO WATCH.
YES, WATCH!
WATCH!
I WAS TASKED WITH THE PAROLE
OF HOLDING THE BODY OF THE
ROOSTER AS OZZY SWUNG THE
MACHETE.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
OZZY SAID, "COCHRAN, YOU'RE
HOLDING THE CHICKEN."
I MEAN, THAT'S KIND OF WHAT IT'S
LIKE AROUND CAMP.
IT'S A LOT OF ORDERS FOR
COCHRAN.
APPARENTLY I WAS HOLDING IT
IN A WAY THAT OZZY FOUND
ENTERTAINING.
I SHOULDN'T BE LAUGHING.
COCHRAN.
YOU WERE HOLDING IT LIKE-- AND
IT WAS-- OH, MY GOD.
I SHOULD NOT BE LAUGHING.
AND I'M SORRY I'M LAUGHING BUT
IT IS JUST-- I CAN'T HELP BUT
HAVE THE IMAGE BURNED INTO MY
MIND OF COCHRAN STANDING THERE
HOLDING IT WITH HIS EYES CLOSED
AND HIS MOUTH OPEN.
MY MOUTH WAS OPEN?
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S SO GROSS.
I FELT FOR THE ROOSTER
BECAUSE I COULD SEE THAT WE'RE
NOT THAT DIFFERENT.
I'M JUST HOPING I DON'T HAVE THE
EXACT SAME FATE HE DOES.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE I MISSED
THAT.
I HAVEN'T BEEN PLAYING THE
GAME SO FAR BUTS THIS BECAUSE
THIS HAS BEEN THE TEAM GAME, THE
TRIBE GAME.
I ALWAYS KNEW I WAS GOING TO BE
HORRIBLE AT THE TRIBE GAME.
MERGE TIME IS WHEN I WILL
SUCCEED.
I WILL SLIVER IN AND OUT OF
EVERY ALLIANCE, CUT BONDS.
AND WHEN THE MERGE COMES IF I'M
STILL HERE, YOU'RE GOING TO SEE
IT HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE IT HAPPEN.
Jeff: GO!
WITH THE MERGE JUST AROUND THE
CORNER.
MOVE IT!
Jeff: SAVAII BLEW A PIVOTAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
WE DID IT IT IT!
WE DID IT!
Jeff: AFTER THE LOSS--
I'M PUTTING MY LIFE ON THE
LINE.
Jeff: YOU'RE SAYING YOU'RE
GOING TO GO TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
YES.
Jeff: OZZY DREW UP A PLAN
SO RIDICULOUS THAT IT JUST MIGHT
WORK.
I'M GOING TO TELL CHRISTINE
THAT COCHRAN, THE LITTLE SMART
KEYSLE HE IS, FOUND THE IDOL,
KEPT IT FROM US.
WE GO TO VOTE HIM OUT, HE WHIPS
OUT THE IDOL, SEE YOU LATER,
OZZY.
NOT ONLY IS COCHRAN THE VILLAIN,
BUT HE'S NOW THE DOUBLE AGENT.
Jeff: OZZY'S PLAN SENT ONE
OF THE GREATEST COMPETITORS IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
TO BATTLE IT OUT AGAINST
CHRISTINE, WHO WAS ON A ROLL,
HAVING WON FIVE DUELS IN A ROW.
AT THE DUEL-- OZZY HAS ALL THREE
KEYS.
CHRISTINE HAS NONE.
CHRISTINE FELL TO FIVE AND ONE.
OZZY WINS THE DUEL AND IS BACK
IN THIS GAME.
YES!
Jeff: AND THE FIRST PART OF
OZZY'S GAMBLE PAID OFF.
YOU AND EVERYBODY ELSE HERE CAN
DROP THEIR BUFFS BECAUSE WE ARE
MERGED.
AND WHEN THE TWO TRIBES MERGED--
LOOKING GOOD.
Jeff: COACH WAS LESS THAN
IMPRESSED BY HIS RIFLE OZZY'S
SURVIVOR SKILLS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO ABOUT
THE SLEEPING.
I.
I WAKE UP AND LIKE BUGS
CRAWLING ON ME.
THERE'S BUGS ALL ON YOU.
IS THAT WHAT YOU SAID?
YEAH, USUALLY.
WE WERE ALMOST EXACTLY WHERE
THE MAT IS.
WE'VE BEEN DOING IT UNDER THE
STARS.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
OZZY HAS PLAYED THIS GAME
BEFORE.
THESE OTHER PEOPLE, THEY DON'T
KNOW ANY BETTER.
"SURVIVOR" IS NOT SLEEPING ON
THE FLOOR GETTING BIT UP BY
MOSQUITOES AND ALLING KINDS OF
BUGS.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE A BEACH BUM
AND CAN SLEEP ON THE SAND
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN DOING THAT
YOUR WHOLE LIFE DOES NOT MEAN
YOU SUBJECT YOUR TRIBE TO THAT.
IS THIS WHERE THE COOL PEOPLE
SLEEP?
YEAH.
WHERE DO YOU SLEEP?
NOT IN HERE.
KEITH AND WHITNEY TYPICALLY
SLEEP IN HERE?
WHO ELSE?
SOMETIMES THERE'S A THIRD
PERSON.
I AT ONE POINT A THIRD PERSON.
I GUESS I TOSS AND TURN TOO
MUCH.
IT'S ANNOYING.
SO I'VE BEEN EJECTED.
THIS IS PATHETIC.
YOU HAVE A LOVEMAKING COUPLE
OVER THERE WITH WHITNEY AND
KEITH SHACKING UP IN THEIR OWN
LITTLE LOVE NEST?
WHO LIVES LIKE THAT?
WHO ALLOWS PEOPLE TO LIVE LIKE
THAT?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
OZZY NO WONDER YOU NEVER WON
"SURVIVOR."
YOU'RE A FRIGGING IDIOT.
OZZY YOU CALL YOURSELF AN
ALL-STAR SURVIVOR AND YOU WANT
TOW COME HERE AND BUILD A
SHELTER LIKE THAT?
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF
YOURSELF.
Jeff: ON THE NEWLY FORMED
TE TUNA'S TRIBE FIRST NIGHT, THE
FORMER UPOLUS WERE RESTLESS.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
I'D RATHER SLEEP DOWN FROM A
GARBAGE DUMP THAN THE FIRE.
( LAUGHTER )
THAT FIRE KILLS YOU.
I FEEL LIKE I'M GOING TO
BARF.
IT IS.
WE'LL PUT A "SNOW SMOKING" SIGN
UP.
Jeff: BUT COACH LOOKED PAST
THE SMOKE AND SAW AN
OPPORTUNITY.
COCHRAN IS SLEEPING BY
HIMSELF.
JIM AND DAWN ARE CUDDLED UP NEXT
TO EACH OTHER WITH A PILLOW AND
BLANKET.
WHITNEY AND KEITH ARE COVERED UP
WITH A PILLOW AND A BLANKET, AND
OZZY IS SLEEPING BY THE FIRE.
I MEAN, HOW MESSED UP IS THAT?
SOMEBODY LIKE COCHRAN.
THAT BOY DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO
SURVIVE OUT HERE.
THAT IS NOT GOING TO STAND ON
COACH WADE'S WATCH.
THAT KIND OF STUFF PISSES ME
OFF.
YOU KNOW WHAT, COCHRAN?
COME OVER HERE.
I'VE GOT ROOM UNDER MY WING FOR
YOU.
Jeff: THE NEXT MORNING
COACH USED ALL OF HIS STAR POWER
TO BEDAZZLE COCHRAN TO
CONTEMPLATING A JUMP FROM SIXTH
AT SAVAII TO SIEVING AT UPOLU.
GIVE ME A HUG, MAN.
GIVE ME A HUG.
HOW YOU FEELING, MAN?
FEELING GOOD.
HUH?
YOU READY FOR A LITTLE CHAT,
MAN?
YOU MIND BREAKING AWAY?
NO STRATEGY IT'S MYTHOLOGY.
MYTHOLOGY.
GREEK MYTHOLOGY.
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
DO I HAVE TO KNEEL FOR THIS?
I WILL BE THE ONE KNEELING,
MAN.
I IDENTIFY WITH COCHRAN FOR SO
MANY LEVELS.
I SEE SOMEBODY NOT BLESSED WITH
THE BEST FEZEEB.
I SEE SOMEBODY BLESSED WITH AN
INCREDIBLE MIND.
IMAGINE WHAT HIS LIFE HAS BEEN
LIKE.
IMAGINE WHAT HIS SELF-ESTEEM HAS
BEEN LIKE.
NOBODY HAS GIFTEN HIM
SELF-CONFIDENCE IN HIS LIFE
OUTSIDE HIS FAMILY.
ANYTHING I CAN DO TO GIVE HIM
COURAGE AND MAKE HIM FEEL VALUED
AND PROSPECTS, I WILL DO.
THIS IS A MIXTURE OF GREEK
MYTHOLOGY, AND GREEK HISTORY.
BUT YOU HAVE TO AGREE TO LIKE
THESE NAMES, OKAY?
ABSOLUTELY.
NOT YOUR NAME.
THAT'S-- THAT'S NOT QUESTIONED.
YOU HAVE NAMES FOR DIFFERENT
PEOPLE?
YES, THAT'S THE THING AND I
NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD USE IT--
WE'LL START WITH OZZY.
OKAY.
OKAY?
WITHOUT QUESTION, OZZY ISINAR
SISIS, BECAUSE AS YOU KNOW THE
STORY, WHENINAR SISIS LOOKED
INTO THE WATER BECAUSE HE WAS SO
INFATUATED WITH HIMSELF HE
BECAME UNAWARE OF THE WORLD
AROUND HIM.
WHITNEY IS EROTO, AND SHE WAS
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL OF THE NINE.
THE NEXT ONE WOULD BE EDNA.
I SAID SHE IS ECHO.
AND ECHO, OBVIOUSLY, SPOKE SO
MUCH--
COACH CAME UP WITH IDENTITIES
FOR EVERY SINGLE MEMBER OF THE
TE TUNA TRIBE.
AND A LOT OF THEM ARE NOT SO
FLATTERING.
FINALLY, AT LAST, YOU ARE THE
MOST POWERFUL MAN IN THE GAME.
OKAY?
OKAY.
REALLY.
WHO IS THE MOST POWERFUL GOD?
WHO WAS THE STRONGEST, STRONGEST
MAN ON EARTH THEY CALLED HIM?
HERCULES.
YEAH.
I'M HERCULES.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
THE RAGING BULL OF MINOS WAS
STRONGER THAN HERCULES AND &
WHAT HERCULES DID THAT MOST
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW IS HE USED HIS
BRAIN TO BEAT THE BULL.
HE MOUNTED THE BULL AND FORCED
IT TO SWIM UP THE RIVER ALL THE
WAY TO THE CAPITAL, AND BY THE
TIME THEY HAD GOTTEN TO THE
CAPITAL, THE BULL WAS TIRED.
HERCULES JUMPED OFF OF HIM AND
SLEW HIM.
THAT IS VERY APPROPRIATE.
IT'S EXTREMELY APPROPRIATE.
DAMN RIGHT IT'S APPROPRIATE.
COACH IN DUBBING ME HERCULES
IS QUITE LITERALLY ENTERED ME
INTO THE PANTHON OF "SURVIVOR"
GOD.
I'VE EARNED HIS RESPECT AND
TRUST AND NOW I'M WEARING THE
ICONIC COACH JACKET, THE FLORAL
PATTERNS.
I'M SURE THERE'S SOME SORT OF
DRAGON INSIGNIA SOMEWHERE ON
HERE AND I FEEL LIKE THE DRAGON
BLOOD THAT FLOWS THROUGH HIS
VEINS IS ENTERING MY POURS AND
MY BLOOD STREAM.
I THOUGHT MY NAME SHOULD BE
ZEUS BECAUSE ZEUS IS FOGERLY,
RIGHT?
HE LOOKS AFTER EVERYBODY, AND IF
SOMEBODY WRONGS ONE OF HIS
CHILDREN, HE IS RUTHLESS IN
RETRIBUTION.
I LIKE THAT.
I'M ONE OF YOUR CHILDREN.
DESPITE COACH'S CLAIMS THAT ZEUS
IS A DOTING FATHER, I SEEM TO
THINK ZEUS ATE HIS CHILDREN, AND
IF HE VIEWS ME AS ONE OF HIS
CHILDREN, AS HE KIND OF
REPEATEDLY HAS, I'M FEARING THAT
COACH AT SOME POINT MAY DEVOUR
ME.
ZEUS, HERCULES.
Jeff: COMING UP NEXT--
LET'S EAT THE CHICKEN.
WHAT ELSE CAN YOU DO?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
SON OF A GUN!
THERE'S A POINT IN TIME WHEN
YOU SCREW UP AND YOU HAVE TO
TAKE OWNERSHIP OF THAT ACTION.
YOU STILL HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY
TO COME WITH US.
YOU HAVE MY WORD ME AND YOU TO
THE END.
DUDE, WAS I BORN YESTERDAY?
OZZY WAS LYING.
Jeff: EVERYONE KNOWS OZZY'S
STRENGTHS ARE IN CHALLENGES AND
PROVIDING, BUT FOR HIM TO FIND
REDEMPTION, HE KNEW THAT HE
NEEDED TO PLAY A BETTER SOCIAL
GAME.
ON DAY 20, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A
GREAT MOVE IF HE HAD USED HIS
TALENTS TO MAKE SOME FRIEND
AMONG THE OLD UPOLU TRIBE.
I'VE BEEN THE PROVIDER FOR MY
TRIBE SINCE THE FIRST FREAKING
WEEK OF THIS GAME, BUT ONCE YOU
GET TO THE MERGE, BEING A
PROVIDER REALLY IS A LIABILITY.
I ONLY GOT THREE WE'RE MERGED
TOGETHER AND THERE'S 12 OF US,
AND PART OF ME WAS THINKING,UN,
IT'S A SHAME THAT I'VE GOT TO
SHARE ALL THIS FOOD WITH THE
FORMER UPOLU MEMBERS THAT
BASICALLY VOTING AGAINST US.
SO I'M JUST TRYING TO KEEP MY
TRIBE STRONG AND UNIFIED AS MUCH
AS POSSIBLE.
I DON'T KNOW, SHOULD WE JUST EAT
THE FISH US, OR WHAT?
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY LIKE
THAT, DO YOU?
IT ALWAYS GETS TOUGH TO FEED
THE COMPETITION.
I'M TOTALEE TRIBE.
IT'S HARD FOR ME TO BE--
YEAH, YEAH.
MEAN.
YEAH.
AND THAT FEELS MEAN FOR ME,
SO I'M GOOD.
I'M TOTALLY THE SAME TRIBE.
I'M JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO DO IT AND NOT FEEL LIKE
AN ASS.
YOU'RE RIGHT YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S SUCH A SELFISH GAME AT THE
END OF THE DAY, AND I THINK I'M
REALIZING TODAY THAT, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE BEING A MOM OF SIX IS--
I'M NOT USED TO BEING SO FOIXED
ON PRESERVING MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE THE BEST THING
YOU CAN DO AS A PARENT IS TAKE
CARE OF EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU FOR GETTING THAT.
FEEDING THE COMPETITION IS
KIND OF A WEIRD IDEA.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YEAH, IT'S UNDERSTANDABLE.
JUST DON'T WIN.
THAT WAS A LITTLE BIT RUDE.
AND I DON'T LOOK AT YOU GUYS AS
ENEMIES BY THE WAY.
I GIVE OZZY A LOT OF CREDIT.
HE IS BY FAR THE BEST PHYSICAL
PLAYER HERE ON THIS ISLAND.
IT'S GOING TO BE GOOD, MAN.
IT'S NOT HOW YOU START, THOUGH.
IT'S HOW YOU FINISH.
AND IF HE IS WANTING TO DO THE
WRONG THING, PLAY THE GAME FOR
HIMSELF, I THINK IT'S DEFINITELY
GOING TO BITE HIM IN THE BUTT.
I KNOW HOW TO PLAY THAT GAME.
THANK YOU AGAIN FOR THIS, MAN.
OF COURSE.
I'LL GO WITH IT BECAUSE OZZY
IS GOING HOME.
Jeff: ON KAY 21, OZZY WON
IMMUNITY AND WAS SAFE AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SO HE TRIED TO USE HIS SOCIAL
GAME TO PLAY COACH.
LITTLE DID HE KNOW, COACH WAS
PLAYING HIM, TOO.
YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
YOU GUYS ARE LOOKING PRETTY
GOOD, MAN.
IT'S PRETTY MUCH NOT IN OUR
FAVOR, MAN.
YOU GUYS-- OH, MAN.
WORST-CASE SCENARIO, MAN, IS
THAT YOU GUYS WOULD WIN.
I KNOW.
I HATE IT, MAN.
I HATE IT.
I KNOW.
IT'S--
I WANTED TO PLAY THIS GAME SO
BAD WITH YOU, MAN.
YEAH, AND I MEAN, YOU STILL
HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO COME WITH
US.
AND I WOULD GUARANTEE YOU COMING
TO THE END WITH ME.
I WOULD SCREW MY TRIBE OVER.
THIS COULD POSSIBLY SECURE THE
TOP SIX.
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS ON OUR SIDE.
AND I HOPE COACH SEES THE
WRITING ON THE WALL.
I WILL BASICALLY GUARANTEE COACH
THE FINAL TWO.
NOT REALLY, BUT OF COURSE THAT'S
WHAT I HAVE TO TELL HIM.
YOU HAVE MY WORD THAT ME AND YOU
TO THE END.
AND ALL I CAN DO IS OFFER YOU
THAT.
DUDE, WAS I BORN YESTERDAY?
ABSOLUTELY, OZZY.
LET'S PLAY THIS GAME TOGETHER
AND LET ME JUST VOTE OFF MY
TRIBE.
NICCI ONCE SAID WHEN YOU HAVE
MORE ARROGANCE, YOU HAVE LESS
WISDOM.
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU TALKING
TO ME.
ESPECIALLY SINCE YOU HOLD ALL
THE CARDS.
I DON'T EVER WANT TO SAY COACH
IS IN CONTROL BUT I REALLY THINK
I'M IN CONTROL.
IN THIS GAME THE WEAK WILL
BECOME THE STRONG AND THE STRONG
WILL BECOME THE WEAK.
THAT'S WHAT COCHRAN WILL DO FOR
THE GAME.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHEN COCHRAN DID FLIP HE TOOK
OUT ONE OF HIS OWN.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT THE
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC."
OZZY, ONCE AGAIN, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
EVEN WITH SAVAII'S NUMBERS
DWINDLING, KEEPING THE UPOLU
FAMILY INTACT WAS A CONSTANT
STRUGGLE.
BY DAY 23, BRANDON'S ANTICS WERE
LEADING TO INCREASINGLY GREATER
CONCERNS THAT HE WAS BECOMING A
LIABILITY.
I WONDER IF THEY GOT REQUEST
FISH.
PROBABLY NOT.
HOW TO GO, BRANDON!
OZZY WAS AMAZING AT CATCHING
FISH.
YOU KNOW, YOU GOTTA GIVE THE MAN
HIS PROPS.
I TRIED TO CATCH FISH OUT HERE.
THIS CURRENT IS CRAZY.
SOMETIMES THE CURRENT IS TOO BAD
TO EVEN GO OUT.
I WAS UNSUCCESSFUL.
THANKS FOR GOING OUT.
EVERYONE HERE IS ABSOLUTELY
STARVING.
WE DON'T HAVE HAVE MANY OPTIONS
AS FAR AS FOOD IS CONCERNED
RIGHT NOW.
BUT WE DO HAVE THE CHICKENS.
THAT WILL MAKE US ONE LITTLE
BITE.
DUDE, WE'RE GOING TO EAT A
PIECE OF EGG ABOUT THIS BIG.
LET'SING BE REAL.
WE EAT COCONUTS WITH
EVERYTHING, MAN.
THEN LET'S EAT THE CHICKEN.
LET'S KILL THE CHICKEN.
YEAH, I THINK WE SHOULD.
I MADE MY DECISION AND I MADE
IT KNOWN.
LET'S KILL THE CHICKEN.
LET'S EAT THE CHICKEN.
SON OF A GUN.
HEY!
NO GOOD.
HEY, GET THAT CHICK OWN THIS
SIDE, GUYS!
SMART CHICKEN.
HE GRABBED BY THE FEATHERS.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO GRAB BY THE
FEET.
IT'S A CHICKEN, YOU GRAB IT BY
THE NECK AND SPIN IT AROUND AND
KILL IT OR BITE ITS HEAD OFF.
IF YOU WANT TO BE COOL, STRETCH
IT OUT AND BITE IT.
SON OF A GUN.
THIS SUCKS.
AND WITHSTANDON, WHO IS ALREADY
IN A BAD MOOD, IS THE ONE WHEN
LET CHICKEN GO SO HE'S GOING TO
GO... AND DO A DOWNWARD SPIRAL.
WE'RE NOT KILLING THAT ONE, ARE
WE?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
KILLING A CHICKEN AT THIS
POINT IS NOT THE SMARTEST THING
TO DO.
WE GO FROM TWO CHICKENS TO
ZERO CHICKENS IN, LIKE, 20
SECONDS HERE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT, GUYS.
HAVING ZERO CHICKENS BECAUSE
ONE FLEW THE COOP AND THE OTHER
IS NOW DEAD IS PREPORTEROUS.
AND THERE'S A POINT IN TIME YOU
SCREW UP AND YOU HAVE TO TAKE
OWNERSHIP OF THAT ACTION.
I GRABBED HIM AND HE JUST-- I
SHOULD HAVE GRABBED HIM BY THE
NECK.
THE WHEELS ARE SLOWLY BUT
SURELY STARTING TO COME OFF THE
BRANDON HANTZ TRAIN.
HE'S SO INTULSIVE SOMETIMES.
HE'S ONLY A KID.
HE'S 19 YEARS OLD.
YOU HAVE TO CORAL HIM A LOT OF
TIMES AND REEL HIM BACK IN BUT I
DON'T KNOW IF I FEEL THAT
COMFORTABLE INVESTING MY TRUST
IN HIM, INVEST MY WELL-BEING IN
THE GAME.
I'M SORRY, BROTHER.
BRANDON LOSING THE CHICKEN.
MAYBE BRANDON CAN PRAY FOR IT
AND IT WILL SHOW BACK UP.
Jeff: BRANDON'S INSTABILITY
WASN'T THE ONLY THREAT FACING
COACH'S LEADERSHIP.
ALBERT'S SELFISH AMBITIONS
BUBBLED TO THE SURFACE WHEN HE
PITCHED SOVIETO A PLOT TO BREAK
UP THE FAMILY.
IF WE GET BRANDON NEXT, USING
WHITNEY AND DAWN WHO ARE GOING
TO BE SCRAMBLING TO DO ANYTHING.
OBVIOUSLY WE CAN'T DO THAT
RIGHT NOW.
HE'S AN EXTREMELY DANGEROUS
PERSON.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD VOTE
OUT BRANDON FIRST.
THERE'S NO POINT.
BRANDON COULD WIN IMMUNITY.
I'M NOT TERRIFIED THAT
BRANDON IS GOING TO GO ON AN
IMMUNITY WIN.
HE'S NOT.
I THINK ALBERT THINKS HE HAS
THIS GREAT STRATEGIC MIND AND I
DON'T THINK HE'S COME UP WITH
ONE GOOD PLAN YET.
HIS RECENT PLAN IS GET RID OF
BRANDON SOONER.
I DON'T SEE THE IN THAT.
EVERYONE IS GOING TO GO ALONG
WITH GETTING OUT SAVAII.
WITH GETTING OUT BRANDON.
THE LAST THING I WANT IS FOR
THINGS TO BE SHAKEN UP.
WHAT'S THE POINT IN PISSING
BRANDON OFF.
HE COULD COME BACK.
I THINK MIXING THINGS UP THIS
EARLY IS CRAZY BECAUSE PEOPLE
LIKE RICK ARE GOING TO SAY WE
SCREWED THINGS UP.
ALBERT IS THE ONE WHO IS ALWAYS
FEELING UNCOMFORTABLE.
HE IS ALSO WANTING TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE.
YOU GO AGAINST THIFY, YOU GO
AGAINST THE SIX.
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO THROW YOU
IN THE FIRE.
WE'LL CHOP YOUR HEAD OFF.
Jeff: 10 CASTS WAYS ARE
LEFT AS THE END DRAWS NEAR.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOUR LAST
DAY HERE BE FILLED WITH
BITTERNESS.
Jeff: CAN AN UNDERDOG
OUTWIT THE MAIORITY.
WHICH CASTAWAYS WILL MAKE IT
TO THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THEN I CANT TRUST COACH THEN.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DO THIS
FOR ME?
AFTER ALL I'VE DONE FOR YOU,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DO THIS FOR
ME.
Jeff: WHICH ALLIANCE WILL
OUTLAST THE REST.
I DON'T FEEL INDEBTED TO YOU.
Jeff: AS THE ADVENTURE
CONTINUES.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
EVERYBODY'S FIGHTING TO BE
STANDING AT THE BITTER END.
YOU MAKE ME HAPPY TO SEE YOU
GO FATHER THAN RICK IN THIS
GAME.
ARE YOU GOING TO BE MY
FRIEND?
UNLESS YOU STAB ME IN THE
BACK.
I'M ON BOARD.
WE CAN KICK HIM OFF.
WITH MY LAST DYING BREATH, I
WILL FIGHT TO KEEP MY YOUNG
WARRIOR.
Y.
KEITH ALWAYS HAS THIS WAY OF
TALKING TO ME AND EVERYTHING HE
SAYS IS A SPORTS METAPHOR.
YOU CAN'T REANALYZE LIKE
THAT, COCHRAN.
YOU CAN'T REQUEST TO COURT LIKE
THAT.
YOU KEEP ASKING QUESTIONS.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP YOUR GAME
FACEO, GAME MODE, SPORT MODE OR
YOU'RE GOING TO FUMBLE.
YOU CAN'T FUMBLE IN THE GAME OF
LIFE MAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU DO WHEN
YOU'RE BACK ON THE COURT AT
HOME.