Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": BY DAY 15, CHRISTINE
HAD BECOME A FORCE TO BE
RECKONED WITH.
CHRISTINE WINS HER FOWRPGHT DUEL
AND STAYS ALIVE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
AND SHE WAS DANGEROUSLY CLOSE TO
WINNING HER WAY BACK INTO THE
GAME.
I CAN DO IT.
Jeff: AT SAVAII, OOZY WAS
ON THE OUTS WITH HIS TRIBE.
I AM NOW A FREE AGENCY.
Jeff: BUT AFTER A BIG WIN--
SAVAII WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
THEY ALL KISSED AND MADE UP.
ONE, TWO, THREE, SAVAII!
Jeff: AT UPOLU, MIKAYLA WAS
THE ONLY PERSON NOT IN THE
ALLIANCE OF SIX, SO COACH WANTED
HER VOTED OUT.
BUT ALBERT AND SOPHIE WANTED TO
GET RID OF EDNA.
EDNA HAS ZERO CHALLENGE
VALUE, ZERO.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
BRANDON ERUPTED, MAKING IT THE
THIRD TRIBAL IN A ROW WHERE HE
HAS SUFFERED A MELTDOWN.
VOTE ME OUT TODAY IF WE WERE
GOING TO PLAY DISLOYAL.
DISLOYAL.
Jeff: BUT DESPITE OUTBURST,
MIKAYLA AVES SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
WITH BOTH TRIBES NOW EVEN AND A
MERGE LOOMING, THE OUTCOME OF
THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
COULD CHANGE THE GAME.
IT'S NOT A GOOD FEELING TO
HAVE YOUR NAME COME UP ON THE
VOTE EVERY SINGLE TIME YOU'RE AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BRANDON'S REACTION AND HIS
UNPREDICT ABLG NATURE IS A
LIABILITY, YES.
DEFINITELY.
AND IF HE CONTINUES THIS WAY,
HE-- HE'S MAKING MY JOB ON
"SURVIVOR" EASIER BY JUST BEING
HIMSELF.
IF THERE COMES A TIME WHERE
BRANDON BECOMES A LIABILITY,
JUST LIKE OLD LENNY OF "MICE AND
MEN" THERE COMES A TIME WHERE
YOU GOT TO PUT A BULLET IN
SOMEBODY'S HEAD EXPWHRK IN THIS
GAME, IT'S KILL OR BE KILLED.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
♪ ♪ ♪
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
CHRISTINE WILL BATTLE AGAINST
MIKAYLA, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
DUEL?
YEAH.
Jeff: FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU
WILL TAKE APART A CRATE AND USE
THE PLANKS TO BUILD A BRIDGE.
ONCE YOU'VE COMPLETED THE
BRIDGE, YOU'LL TAKE THE BRIDGE
APART AND USE SOME OF THOSE
PLANKS TO SOLVE A PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
SAYS ALIVE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
LOSER IS OUT OF THE GAME FOR
GOOD.
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
FIRST STEP IS TO TAKE ALL THE
PLANKS OFF OF THAT CRATE.
CHRISTINE FIGURING OUT A SYSTEM
QUICKLY.
CHRISTINE TAKES OUT A WHOLE SIDE
IN ONE SWOOP.
PICK IT UP FROM THE.
GRAB FROM THE BOTTOM.
Jeff: CHRISTINE HAS ALL HER
PLANKS.
SHE'S GOING TO START PUTTING
THIS BRIDGE TOGETHER.
THIS BRIDGE IS A PUZZLE IN AND
OF ITSELF.
MIKAYLA HAS ALL HER PLANKS NOW.
SHE'S TARTING TO WORK ON HER
BRIDGE.
GOTTA PUT THEM IN ORDER, BILLION
THAT BRIDGE FROM START TO
FINISH.
THIS IS A DO-OR-DIE DUEL.
CHRISTINE ADDS ANOTHER PLANK.
MIKAYLA ADDS ANOTHER PLANK.
BOTH WOMEN GETTING INTO A
RHYTHM.
THEY'RE BACK AND FORTH NOW.
CHRISTINE STILL WITH THE LEAD
BUT MIKAYLA NOT LETTING HER PULL
AHEAD.
CHRISTINE VERY CLOSE TO
FINISHING HER BRIDGE.
THE RIDE SIDE!
THE RIGHT SIDE!
THATTA GIRL.
Jeff: MIKAYLA GETTING HELP
FROM HER FORMER TRIBEMATES.
CHRISTINE WITH ONE PIECE LEFT.
MIKAYLA STILL HAS FOUR.
ONCE YOU FINISH IT, TAG OUT.
GO BACK, START TAKING IT APART.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR PATTERN
PIECES.
THE ONES THAT HAVE A PATTERN ARE
PART OF YOUR PUZZLE.
IF THEY'RE BLANK, YOU DON'T NEED
THEM.
MIKAYLA NOW WITH ONE PLANK LEFT.
THIS WILL FINISH HER BRIDGE.
TAG OUT, COME BACK.
MIKAYLA NOW START TAKING YOUR
BRIDGE APART.
TOSS THE GOOD ONES AT THE
BOX.
Jeff: CHRISTINE'S GOT A BIT
OF A LEAD.
SHE'S WON FOUR DUELS IN A ROW.
CHRISTINE HAS ALL OF HER PLANKS.
SHE'S GOING TO START WORKING ON
THE PUZZLE.
MIKAYLA HAS ALL OF HER PIECES.
BOTH WOMEN WORKING ON THE PUZZLE
NOW.
YOU'LL RECOGNIZE THIS SYMBOL.
IT IS THE REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA SYMBOL.
THERE ARE ALWAYS CLUES.
BOTH WOMEN RACING TO PUT THIS
PUZZLE TOGETHER.
MIKAYLA THINKS SHE HAS IT.
NO, MIKAYLA'S NOT RIGHT.
SOMETHING'S JUST OFF.
LOOK AT IT.
TAKE A MOMENT.
WHAT'S OFF?
WHERE ARE THE PATTERNS?
WHERE ARE THE CLUES?
ADJUST AND TRY AGAIN.
JEFF, JEFF, JEFF.
Jeff: CHRISTINE THINKS SHE
HAS IT.
CHRISTINE STAYS ALIVE ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND!
OH, MY GOD.
( APPLAUSE )
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
AMAZING JOB.
Jeff: WHAT'S DIFFERENT AS A
RESULT OF THIS ADVENTURE FOR
YOU, MIKAYLA?
OUT HERE, YOU KNOW, IT MAKES
ME REALIZE HOW MUCH STRONGER I
WANT TO BE AND HOW MUCH BETTER I
WANT TO BE.
Jeff: MIKAYLA, YOUR
ADVENTURE HAS COME TO AN END.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
RAISE HELL, BABY.
I WILL, FOR YOU.
Jeff: CHRISTINE, YOU HAVE
SINGLEHANDEDLY SENT FIVE PEOPLE
OUT OF THIS GAME.
CRAZY.
Jeff: YOU'RE BECOMING A
LEGITIMATE FORCE.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A LEGITIMATE
FORCE.
Jeff: ALWAYS BEEN A
LEGITIMATE FORCE.
MY WHOLE LIFE.
Jeff: WITH EACH WIN, YOU'RE
GETTING CLOSER TO GETTING BACK
INTO THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION.
WAIT FOR YOUR NEXT DUEL.
CHRISTINE HAS BEEN ON A HOT
STREAK.
SHE HAS WON FIVE DUELS IN A ROW.
WHEN WE MERGE, SHE COULD GO TO
THE OTHER SIDE OR SHE COULD COME
WITH US.
PEOPLE ARE THINKING THE MERGE IS
COMING AFTER THE NEXT CHALLENGE.
SO IF WE LOSE THE NEXT CHALLENGE
TMIGHT BE WORTHWHILE FOR US TO
SEND SOMEBODY TO REDEMPTION THAT
CAN BEAT CHRISTINE, COME BACK IN
THE GAME, AND EVEN OUT THE
NUMBERS.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE BIG
MOVES IN THIS GAME, AND IF WE
HAVE TO, THAT MIKE A BIG MOVE
WORTH MAKING.
YOU KNOW,US OF US BEING IN
THIS POSITION WE'RE IN, WE'RE ON
DIFFERENT, OPPOSITE POLES BUT
STILL THE SAME SIDE OF THE LOOP.
WE SHOULD HELP EACH OTHER AS
MUCH AS WE CAN.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS GOING TO
SAY.
THE ONLY THING I'M WORRIED
ABOUT, CHRISTINE WON TODAY.
IF-- IF WE DON'T WIN WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO SEND SOMEBODY INTO
REDEMPTION.
COCHRAN AND I GOT BACK FROM THE
DUEL, AND I WANTED TO LET
COCHRAN IN ON MY WORST-CASE
SCENARIO PLAN.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO SEND?
WELL, THE THING IS, IS WE
HAVE TO SEND SOMEBODY WHO WE
KNOW CAN BEAT HER.
THAT WAY WE CAN GET OUR NUMBERS
BACK.
YEAH.
I DON'T WANT TO GO TO
REDEMPTION, BUT IF IT COMES DOWN
TO IT, IF IT'S LIKE A DO-OR-DIE
SITUATION.
I WILL GO.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
WHAT I'LL HAVE TO DO IS I'LL
HAVE TO TAKE THE IDOL, I'LL HAVE
TO GIVE IT TO SOMEBODY.
HOPEFULLY THEY'LL PROMISE TO
GIVE IT BACK IF I MAKE IT BACK.
SO THEN I WOULD GO TO REF
DEMPTION, HOPEFULLY WIN--
THE GENERAL SENSE AROUND CAMP
IS THAT THE MERGE IS HAPPENING
SOONER RATHER THAN LATER.
AND NOW OZZY SUGGESTED HE'D BE
WILLING TO MAKE A PRETTY BOLD
MOVE IN THE EVENT WE LOSE OUR
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
HE'S CONSIDERING LENDING HIS
HIDDEN IMMINT IDOL TO SOMEBODY
ELSE ON THE TRIBE, ALLOW HIMSELF
TO GET VOTED OFF THE TRIBE SO HE
CAN BE SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA AND DUEL AGAINST KRISTINA,
HOPEFULLY WIN, COME BACK IT OUR
TRIBE AND KEEP OUR NUMBER
INTACT, 6-6 TIE GOING INTO THE
MERGE.
I WAS THINKING IT OVER IN MY
HEAD, AND IT MIGHT BE-- IT MIGHT
BE ONE OF THOSE BIG MOVES THEY
MIGHT HAVE TO MAKE.
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS THAT CAN
HAPPEN, BUT THIS IS, LIKE, MY
WORST-- THIS IS, LIKE,
WORST-CASE SCENARIO.
IT'S AN ADMIRABLE THING, MAN.
SERIOUSLY.
IT'S-- SOMETIMES YOU JUST
GOTTA LIKE SUCK UP AND GO FOR
IT.
NOW OSSIE SEEMS TO HAVE GONE
FROM A BITTER FREE AGENT, TEMPER
TANTRUM THROWING BABY TO A NEW
MAN.
IF OZZY WAS BEING HONEST, WOULD
WILLINGNESS FALL ON HIS SWORD
FOR HIS TRIBE, THAT WOULD BE
GREAT FOR ME BECAUSE THAT WOULD
MEAN I WOULDN'T BE GOING HOME AT
THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THIS TRIBE IS DOWN IN THE
DUMPS.
WE FEEL AFTER THE VOTE LAST
NIGHT THAT WE'RE DIVIDED.
WE FEEL LIKE WE BLEW THE LAST
CHALLENGE, AND WE FEEL LIKE
WE'VE LOST.
WE NEED A SHOT IN THE ARM RIGHT
NOW, AND WE NEED SOMETHING TO
BOOST OUR SPIRITS.
THE ONLY THING WE CAN DO IS TO
SAY, LOOK, GUYS.
WE'VE GOT THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
GO TEAM.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
THERE'S WAVES WITHIN WAVES IN
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR" TO
SURVIVE.
LOOK, HERE'S THE DEAL.
WE'RE UNIFIED.
WE ARE EVEN NUMBERS.
WE'RE GOING INTO A CHALLENGE.
WE'RE PLAYING THE GREATEST GAME
IN THE WORLD.
IT'S A GREAT ADVENTURE.
IT'S NOT OVER TILL IT'S OVER,
AND WE'RE GOING TO WIN IT,
PERIOD.
LOOK, WE'VE GOT A CLUE TO THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AND IT
SAYS IT'S BEHIND A WALL OF
ROOTS, OKAY.
WE KNOW--
SO RIGHT NOW, SOPHIE, ALBERT,
AND I KNOW THAT I HAVE THE IDOL.
IT'S CLOSE TO THE BEACH, BUT
IT'S IN THE JUNGLE.
BUT PEOPLE LIKE RICK AND
BRANDON AND EDNA, WANT TO FIND
THE IDOL, SO WE'VE GOT TO
PRETEND LIKE, LOOK, WE FOUND IT.
FATHER WE ASK THAT YOU WOULD
FIND FAVOR ON US TODAY.
WE ASK FOR A REJUVENATION OF
THIS TRIBE AND WE ASK THAT YOU
WOULD BLESS US AND GIVE US FAVOR
IN THE CHALLENGE.
FATHER, WE NEED A VICTORY.
I ASK THAT YOU WOULD GIVE US A
VICTORY IN THAT NEXT CHALLENGE
IN JESUS' NAME.
YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE PRAYER
THING, FOR ME, IT DOESN'T WEIGH
AS HEAVILY ON MY MIND BECAUSE
I'M NOT THE ONE SPEAKING THE
PRAYER.
I FIND COACH TO BE LITTLE MORE
QUESTIONABLE WHEN HE ACTUALLY IS
THE ONE SAYING, YOU KNOW, "DEAR
GOD, HELP US FIND THE IDOL,"
WHEN HE KNOWS HE HAS THE IDOL IN
HIS POCKET.
IT GIVEES ME A LITTLE BIT OF AN
ICKY FEELING.
IN JESUS' NAME.
AMEN
WHO FOUND THE CLUE?
?ME, THAT'S REALLY AMAZING.
GOOD JOB.
WHAT THE HECK?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
"TRUST FROM TRIBAL BROTHERS AND
SISTERS AND ENSURE SURVIVAL IF
ARE YOU FAMILY WINS FOR AN
AWESOME REWARD AND DESPITE FROM
THE GAME EVERYTHING DEPEND ON
THE BEST PAIR OF TWINS."
WAIT, THERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
SO SOPHIE AND I WENT TO HONOR
THE IDOL.
LO AND BEHOLD IT WAS TWO FOR THE
PRICE OF ONE.
TREE MAIL ROLLED UP ON OUR
DOORSTEP AND NOW WE'RE GOING TO
ROLL UP A VICTORY IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
TODAY YOUR TRIBE WILL
PARTICIPATE YOUR FACES AND FACES
AND BODY
AS WELL AS ADORN YOURSELF IN
YOUR BEST WARRIOR LOOK.
CHOOSE PAIRS OF PLAYERS TO
COMPETE TOGETHER.
THEIR FACE AND BODY PAINTING AND
ATTIRE SHOULD BE IDENTICAL TO
EACH OTHER.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO SWE NEED
TO MAKE A QUICK DETOUR BEFORE WE
GO BACK TO CAMP, GRAB IT, GRAB
THE IDOL AND COME BACK AND SAY
THIS IS OUR DAY.
YEAH.
HEY, GUYS!
EVERYBODY COME IN!
WHAT IS IT?
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, WE HAVE
TWO PIECES OF GREAT NEWS.
YOU FOUND THE IDOL.
LET'S JUST WAIT.
JUST BE COOL.
WE GOT IT, BOYS!
COME ON!
SOVIETY AND COACH.
TAKE A LOOK.
NO WAY!
LOOK AT THAT, BABY!
WE ACTUALLY ALL SAID A
PRAYER, ASKED GOD FOR HELP TO
FIND THE IDOL, AND WE GOT TREE
MAIL.
NOT ONLY DID THEY GET THE TREE
MAIL, WE FOUND THE IDOL, NOT
FIVE MINUTES AFTER WE PRAYED.
PRAY TOGETHER, STAY TOGETHER.
IT'S DEFINITELY AN ADVANTAGE
HAVING THE BIG GUY UPSTAIRS ON
YOUR TRIBE.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
OZZY, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
THE WINNER OF TODAY'S CHALLENGE
WINS IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND WILL HAVE A
ONE-MEMBER ADVANTAGE IN THIS
GAME.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL BE TAKEN FROM HERE TO THE
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC"
CINEMA WHERE YOU WILL ENJOY AN
EXCLUSIVE SNEAK PEEK OF THE NEW
COLOMBIA PICTURE'S MOVIE "JACK
AND JILL" STARRING ADAM SANDLER.
THE MOVIE DOESN'T OPEN UNTIL
NOVEMBER 11 SO IT IS TRULY A
SNEAK PEEK.
AND OF COURSE YOU WILL ENJOY ALL
THE GOODIES THAT GO WITH A
MOVIE-- POPCORN, SODA, CANDY.
THERE IS A CONNECTION BETWEEN
THE MOVIE "JACK AND JILL' AND
THIS, "SURVIVOR."
"JACK AND JILL" IS ABOUT A
EXPWRGHT SISTER.
THEY ARE TWINS.
HE DOESN'T ALSO GET ALONG WITH
HIS TIN BUT IN THE END HE
REALIZES HE NEEDS HIS SISTER TO
SURVIVE IN THE WORLD.
IT IS THE SAME FOR YOU GUYS.
IT IS THE BOND YOU MAKE THAT
WILL GET YOU TO THE END.
YOU HAVE ALREADY DONE A GREAT
JOB OF PAIRING YOURSELVES UP AS
TWINS.
HERE'S HOW IT WILL WORK.
ONE SET OF TWINS WILL BE YOUR
CALLERS.
THE OTHER TWO SET OF TWINS WILL
BE BLINDFOLDED.
USING ONLY VERBAL COMMANDS, THE
CALLERS WERE LEADING BLINDFOLDED
TWINS THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES TO COLLECT A BAG OF
MAPS.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL FOUR BAGS, ONE
SET OF TWINS WILL EMPTY THE BAGS
AND USING ONLY THEIR SENSE OF
TOUCH WILL PAIR UP THE MASKS IN
MATCHING PAIRS.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT WIN
IMMUNITY AND IS HEADED TO THE
CINEMA.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
YEAH.
Jeff: I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
FOR UPOLU, THE CALLERS ARE COACH
AND RICK.
FOR SAVAII, THE CALLERS ARE JIM
AND COCHRAN.
FOR REWARD AND IMMUNITY,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
STAY LOW, GUYS, STAY LOW.
DOWN!
JUST FOLLOW HIM, EDNA.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE ROPE, ED
EDNA.
Jeff: BRANDON AND EDNA FOR
UPOLU.
DUCK, EDNA, DUCK, EDNA!
Jeff: EDNA TAXES A HARD HIT
RIGHT OFF THE BAT, ALMOST
KNOCKED HER OUT.
KEITH TRYING TO DRAG DAWN.
NOW YOU'RE GOOD, GO FORWARD.
TO THE RIGHT, KEITH!
YOU'RE IN THE WRONG HOLE.
BACK, KEITH!
Jeff: KEITH, LONG BODY,
HAVING TROUBLE GETTING THROUGH
THIS COURSE.
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: BRANDON LOOKING FOR
THE FIRST BACK.
LEFT!
RIGHT THERE!
Jeff: AND THEY'VE GOT IT.
BRANDON AND EDNA HAVE THE FIRST
BAG AND THEY'RE HEADING BACK.
YOU GOT IT!
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: BRAND BRANDON AND
EDNA BACK WITH THEIR FIRST BAGS.
KEITH AND DAWN ARE BACK WITH
THEIR FIRST BAGS.
ALBERT AND SOPHIE NOW FOR UPOLU.
GET UP, ALBERT!
COX RAN IS ON THE ROPE
MANAGEMENT FOR SAVAII.
NOW GO UP, UP THE HILL.
LEFT, NOW DOWN.
HERE'S THE PIT.
UP TO THE TOP, UP TO THE TOP.
Jeff: OZZY AND WHITNEY
DIVING THROUGH THE COURSE.
ALBERT!
HANDS UP, ALBERT!
HANDS UP!
GOT IT.
UNTIE IT!
Jeff: ALBERT STUMBLES INTO
THE SECOND BAG.
OZZY, STOP!
RIGHT BEHIND YOUR HEAD.
RIGHT THERE.
Jeff: OZZY HAS THE SECOND
BAG FOR SAVAII.
KEEP GOING.
Jeff: SOPHIE TAKESY A BIG
FALL.
FIVE MORE PACES UNTIL YOU GET
THERE.
YOU'RE NOT THERE YET.
Jeff: UPOLU HAS THEIR
SECOND BAG BACK.
BRAPPEDON AND EDNA HEADING FOR
THEIR THIRD BAG.
OZZY AND WHITNEY HAVE THEIR
SECOND BAG.
HAVE TO GET BACK TO THE MAT.
UNDER, UNDER, UNDER!
NOW, FLY, BRANDON, GO!
DOWN!
Jeff: KEITH AND DAWN
LOOKING FOR THEIR THIRD BAG.
GET UP ON IT!
Jeff: BRANDON HAS THE THIRD
BAG FOR UPOLU.
HE HAS TO GET IT UNTIED.
YOU GOIT!
UNTIE!
Jeff: KEITH HAS THE THIRD
BAG FOR SAVAII.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
GO, GREAT, RUN!
Jeff: DAWN DOWN IN THE
WATER.
KEEP GOING!
NOW UNDER!
OVER!
QUICKLY.
OVER, EDNA.
Jeff: EDNA IS JUST HOLDING
ON TO BRANDON.
OUT OF THE PIT.
Jeff: SAVAII HAS NOW TAKEN
THE LEAD.
KEITH AND DAWN BACK WITH THAT
THIRD BAG FOR SAVAII.
LEFT JUST A LITTLE BIT,
BRANDON.
BRANDON, PUT IT ON THE TABLE.
GET OUT OF THE WAY, GET OUT
OF THE WAY, MAN.
YOU'RE UNHOCKED.
Jeff: COCHRAN HAVING SOME
TROUBLE.
EDNA AND BRANDON HAVE THEIR
THIRD BAG.
DAWN, DAWN, DAWN.
GO ON KNEES.
Jeff: COCHRAN DOING THE
ROPE MANAGEMENT FOR SAVAII, AND
HE'S ALL TANGLED UP NOW.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
JIM NOW COMING DOWN TO HELP.
IT IS CRITIC YOU GET THEM
UNHOOKED PROPERLY.
UPOLU TAKES THE LEAD.
BIG MALFUNCTION FOR SAVAII.
SAVAII STILL STRUGGLING WITH THE
ROPES.
GO STRAIGHT.
GET DOWN, TO YOUR RIGHT.
Jeff: UPOLU LOOKING FOR THE
FOURTH AND FINAL BAG.
SAVAII HAS LOST A TREMENDOUS
AMOUNT OF TIME.
RIGHT THERE!
PLATFORM!
RIGHT THERE, PLATFORM!
GO!
Jeff: ALBERT'S FOUND THE
FOURTH BAG.
HE'S GOT TO GET IT UNTIED.
GO, GO ALBERT!
DOWN!
Jeff: ALBERT IS LOSING A
LOT OF TIME AT THE FOURTH BAG.
STRAIGHT AHEAD?
>>
OZZY AND WHITNEY HAVE NOW
CAUGHT UP.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: ALBERT HAS THE FOURTH
BAG.
HE AND SOPHIE ARE HEADING BACK
FOR UPOLU.
OZOZZY HAS THE FOURTH BAG FOR
SAVAII.
YOU'VE GOT TO MOVE!
OZZY AND WHITNEY REALLY SLOWING
DOWN, ONCE AGAIN HAVING TROUBLE
ON THE ROPE.
ALBERT AND SOPHIE WITH WITH THE
LEAD.
FULL SPEED!
Jeff: OZZY AND WHITNEY
CONTINUE TO STRUGGLE.
COCHRAN WAS IN CHARGE OF GETTING
THEM HOOKED IN, AND HE DID NOT
DO A GOOD JOB.
STRAIGHT!
MOVE IT!
STRAIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU!
PUT IT DOWN!
Jeff: ALBERT AND SOPHIE
HAVE THE FOURTH BAG.
THEY ARE UNTYING THE BAGS NOW,
RELEASING THE MASKS.
OSSIE'S GOING TO UNHOOK AND
REHOOK THE ROPE THE WAY IT
SHOULD HAVE BEEN IN THE FIRST
PLACE.
SOPHIE AND ALBERT WITH A LEAD
NOW.
THEY'RE ALREADY WORKING ON THEIR
MAPS.
WE ASK YOU, FATHER, PLEASE TO
HELP US RIGHT NOW.
GIVE US THIS VICTORY, FATHER, WE
WILL BOW ON OUR KNEES AND GIVE
YOU THE ACKNOWLEDGMENT.
PLEASE, GIVE IT TO YOU.
Jeff: OZZY AND WHITNEY BACK
WITH THEIR FOURTH BAGS.
START UNTYING.
RELEASE THE MASKS.
NOBODY CAN
HELP AT THIS POINT.
ALBERT STARTING TO WORK ON
PAIRING THEM UP.
WHITNEY STARTING TO WORK FOR
SAVAII.
KEEP GETTING THEM OPEN.
PUT IT RIGHT THERE.
PUT IT RIGHT THERE!
ONE'S UPSIDE DOWN, STOP.
Jeff: SOPHIE MAKING AN
ADJUSTMENT.
OZZY AND WHITNEY WORKING.
OKAY?
Jeff: ALBERT AND SOPHIE
THINK THEY HAVE IT.
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
BRANDON, COME HERE, COME
HERE!
COME HERE!
ON YOUR KNEES.
YOU DIDN'T HOOK IT IN RIGHT!
FATHER, WE THANK YOU FOR THIS
VICTORY.
FATHER, WE PRAISE YOUR NAME THAT
WE HAVE PRAISED FOR YOU, WE GIVE
YOU THE GLORY AND HONOR RIGHT
NOW.
EVERYBODY SAYS IN JESUS' NAME.
YEAH!
Jeff: UPOLU,
CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE ).
THANK YOU.
Jeff: COACH, HOW BIG A WIN
IS THIS FOR UPOLU?
THIS CHALLENGE WAS ABOUT
FAMILY, HIDDEN TRUST, SOME
BLINDFOLDS BUT WE GIVE GOD THE
GLORY.
WE PRAYED BEFORE THE CHALLENGE,
DURING THE CHALLENGE, AND WE
GAVE THANKS AND KNELT DOWN
BEFORE HIM WHEN WE WON THE
CHALLENGE.
WE ARE A FAMILY, JEFF.
IT'S A GREAT GROUP OF PEOPLE
WE'RE PLAYING WITH OVER HERE.
Jeff: THE ADVANTAGE GOES TO
UPOLU.
YOU HAVE A ONE-MEMBER ADVANTAGE,
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION A NICE BREAK FROM
THE GAME.
YOU WILL BE TAKEN TO THE
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC"
CINEMA AND YOU WILL ENJOY "JACK
AND JILL."
I LOVE IT!
Jeff: COME GET YOUR
TICKETS.
HAVE A GOOD TIME AT THE MOVIES.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, CONGRATS.
SEE YOU, GUYS.
GOD BLESS ME.
Jeff: OSSIE, THIS THE MOST
INTENSITY I'VE SEEN YET IN A
SEASON THAT HAS BEEN VERY
INTENSE AND VERY CLOSE.
WHAT IS THE FEELING RIGHT NOW
FOR YOU?
PURE FRUSTRATION AND ANGER.
I FEEL LIKE WE ALMOST HAD IT.
WE WERE THERE.
SOMEONE DIDN'T CONNECT THE RIGHT
ROPE TO THE RIGHT PERSON OR
WHATEVER.
& WE WENT DOWNHILL FROM THERE
AND GOT TANGLED UP.
I CAN'T EVEN BIG GWIN TO
DESCRIBE THE FRUSTRATION BECAUSE
WHEN YOU ARE JUST ABOUT TO GRAB
SOMETHING AND IT GETS PULLED OUT
OF YOUR HANDS IT'S THE WORST
FEELING AND YOU IMAGINE AND NOW
WE HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL --
ALL RIGHT, SAVAII, TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL TOMORROW
NIGHT.
BEFORE THE CHALLENGE, OZZY
REASSURED ME IN THE EVENT WE
LOST, OZZY WOULD SAY SEND ME,
OZZY, TO REDEMPTION ISLAND, AND
COME BACK AND RESTORE OUR
NUMBERS.
BUT AFTER I BLEW THE CHALLENGE,
IT SEEMED LIKE THAT PLAN WENT
OUT THE WINDOW.
I KNEW IMMEDIATELY THAT WAS THE
NEXT TARGET.
I REALLY DID FEEL LIKE CRYING
BUT I STAYED AS STRONG AS I
COULD AND PUT UP WITH IT.
WHAT AN ADVENTURE, GUYS.
AWESOME!
"JACK AND JILL, BABY!
AWESOME JOB.
YEAH!
LET'S DO IT!
THIS REWARD AND IMMUNITY IS
SO IMPORTANT FOR OUR TEAM AND WE
FEEL GREAT HAVING THIS PRIVATE
SCREENING OF THE NEW MOVIE WITH
HOT DOGS AND PRETTY MUCH
UNLIMITED CANDY.
HOW WE DOING?
WHERE WERE YOU!
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOREVER FOR
YOU.
THIS PLACE IS CREEPING ME OUT.
SOME TWINS HAVE STRANGE
POWERS AND THEY CAN FEEL WHEN
THE OTHER ONE IS HURT.
LITTLE HARDER.
WHAT!
OH!
"JACK AND JILL" LOVED IT.
I LOVE ADAM SANDLER.
PERSONALLY, I'M A FAN.
THE HOUSE LOOKS AMAZING!
YOU GOT A NEW CHANDELIER?
IT WAS GOOD BECAUSE IT WAS
FUNNY BUT AT THE SAME TIME THERE
WAS A MESSAGE AND THE MESSAGE
WAS, HEY, FAMILY COMES FIRST.
IT'S A GREAT MESSAGE FOR US TO
BE REMINDED THAT GOING INTO
THESE DAYS TO COME, IT WILL GET
TOUGH.
IT WILL GET TO BE A POINT OF
COMPROMISE.
BUT WE HAVE TO BE
UNCOMPROMISABLE AS A UNIT.
UNBREAKABLE, THAT'S WHAT OUR
TRIBE IS, AND NOW WE'RE READY TO
PLAY THE SECOND HAMP OF THIS
GAME.
( APPLAUSE ).
GOOD JOB, EVERYBODY, AGAIN.
I MEAN, IT WAS A DISASTER.
IT WAS A DISASTER.
YOU KNOW THE THING SWE COULD
HAVE WON THAT SO EASILY BECAUSE
WE WERE RIGHT THERE.
IF YOU ALL WANT TO VENT AT
ME, I'M WILLING TO HEAR
EVERYTHING.
I CRIED LIKE A BABY THE WHOLE
WAY BACK.
I FEEL--
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
IT WAS THAT-- WHAT WAS SO
DIFFICULT?
I REALLY DON'T.
SO WE GET BACK TO CAMP AFTER
THIS DEVASTATING LOSS, WHICH I
GUESS, APPARENTLY, I CAUSED.
YOU KNOW, I'VE ALWAYS FELT LIKE
AN OUTCAST ON MY TRIBE, BUT THIS
WAS A REAL-- A HUGE-- THIS WAS--
THIS WAS A NEW LEVEL OF
OFTRASCIZZIM, AND IT FELT
HORRIBLE.
THAT LOSS JUST KILLED ME.
LIKE I'M SAYING, IF YOU WANT
TO VENT AT ME, I'M TAKING IT
ALL.
IT'S ABOUT WHO IS GOING TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AND THAT'S SOMETHING WE COULD
DECIDE AS A GROUP, BECAUSE--
WE HAVE TO DECIDE AS A GROUP
AND THEY HAVE TO AGREE WITH IT.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL RIGHT NOW.
THAT MOMENT, THE HIGH I HAD
BEEN EXPERIENCING FROM THE
KNOWLEDGE THAT, REALLY, I WASN'T
GOING ONLY IN ANY EVENT.
I WAS SAFE, NOBODY WAS GOING TO
KICK ME OFF.
THAT INVOLVEMENTED INSTANTLY,
AND I KNEW IMMEDIATELY THAT I
WAS THE NEXT TARING.
YOU KNOW, I HATE TO SAY
TCOCHRAN, BUT YOU LOST IT FOR
US.
AND I DON'T EVEN WANT TO SAY YOU
LOST IT FOR US, BUT IT WAS-- IT
WAS A HUGE-- IT WAS A HUGE
ERROR.
AND IT ENDED UP COSTING US THE
WIN.
I'M WILLING TO DO WHATEVER.
I FEEL HORRIBLE.
AND, YOU KNOW, I SHOULD BE HELD
ACCOUNTABLE.
IT'S A RISKY MOVE TO SEND
COCHRAN TO REDEMPTION.
IT'S A RISKIER MOVE TO SEND ME
TO REDEMPTION AND HAVE THE MERGE
BE DELAYED ONE MORE CHALLENGE.
COCHRAN VOLUNTEERED TO GO TO
REDEMPTION.
IT'S GOING TO BE HIS CHANCE TO
REDEEM HIMSELF.
COCHRAN, WE ALL BELIEVE YOU CAN
DO IT.
WE DO.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE YOU CAN
DO IT.
THAT'S THE KEY.
BUT YOU GOTTA BELIEVE IN
YOURSELF, MAN.
YOU KNOW, I APPRECIATE THE
WORDS OF ENCOURAGEMENT.
IT'S NOT WORDS OF
ENCOURAGEMENT UPON IT IS THE
IDEA OF REF DEMPTION.
IT REALLY IS.
IT'S TIME TO REDEEM.
INSTEAD OF SENDING OZZY, THE
TROJAN COURSE TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND AND DESTROY CHRISTINE,
THEY'RE SENDING THE COURT
JESTER.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO BE BESIDES A FUNNY
LITTLE DANCE AND MAKE MY HANDS
AROUND IN A COMICAL MANNER.
IT'S NOT GOING TO WIN THE
CHALLENGE AND IT'S PROBABLY NOT
GOING TO GET THAT MANY LAUGHS SO
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE HOPING
FOR.
FEEL IT IN YOUR HEART.
YOU CAN WIN.
EVERYTHING THAT WE CAN
ANTICIPATE.
I MEAN, REALLY, DON'T BE
AFRAID.
YOU'VE GOT TO PUSH FEAR OUT.
EVERYBODY WAS ON ABOARD WITH
VOTING ME OFF, AND WHAT MADE IT
WORSE WAS THEY HAD THIS KIND OF
WEIRD KUMBAYA RATIONALE FOR
VOTING ME OFF THAT ONLY
CONFIRMED THEIR BELIEF THEY
SHOULD GO, SO I'M TERRIFIED.
I DON'T NEED TO BE A HERO AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I DON'T NEED TO BE THE PERSON
THAT SAVES MY TRIBE.
I'M NOT HERE TO BE A HERO.
I'M HERE TO MAKE A AS FAR AS I
CAN, WHETHER THAT MEANS
SLITHERING ON THE GROUND.
I DON'T WANT TO SHINE RIGHT NOW.
I'M WILLING TO SHINE LATER.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GO TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU'RE GOING TO GO THERE, AND
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL CHRISTINE--
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE IS SO PAL
PANEL, THAT CHRISTINE WILL SAY
THAT'S IT.
I'M DONE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I CAN PULL
OFF THE WHOLE, "I'M
INDESTRUCTIBLE TO YOU OF SOW YOU
BETTER BE SHAKING YOUR BOOTS YOU
STUPID BITCH."
HOW YOU DOING, OZZY?
MY HEAD HURTS.
I COULD NOT SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
I BLEW IT.
I'M SORRY.
I WON'T TALK ABOUT IT.
YOU DON'T NEED TO APOLOGIZE
TO ME.
I'M JUST EMBARRASSED.
THAT'S THE BIGGEST THING I'M
FEELING, REALLY.
THAT'S WHY I FEEL LIKE THE
NOTION OF REDEMPTION ISLAND
TAKES ON, LIKE, A LITERAL.
RIGHT?
IT'S TO REDEEM YOURSELF.
YEAH.
YESTERDAY, BEFORE COCHRAN
COST US THE CHALLENGE, I TOLD
HIM THAT I'D BE WILLING TO GO,
SACRIFICE MYSELF, GO TO
REDEMPTION, BEAT CHRISTINE AND
GET BACK IN THIS GAME AND GIVE
OUR TRIBE AN EDGE.
AND LAST NIGHT I HAD SOME CRAZY
DREAMS ABOUT ACTUALLY DOING WHAT
I SAID I WAS GOING TO DO.
I HAD TO BRING THE IDOL OUT OF
MY HIDING SPOT, JUST SO
EVERYBODY REALLY KNOWS THEY
ACTUALLY DO HAVE IT.
I MIGHT AS WELL MAKE A GRAND
ENTRANCE.
EVERYBODY THINKS THAT THIS IS
COCHRAN'S OPPORTUNITY, THAT HE
SHOULD GOING TO REDEMPTION AND
REDEEM HIMSELF BUT I CAME TO
REDEEM MYSELF, SO IT'S MY
OPPORTUNITY, REALLY.
THE QUESTION IS WILL THE TRIBE
GO ALONG WITH MY IDEA?
WOW.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
THAT'S IT.
YOU WANT TO TOUCH IT?
YEAH, GIVE IT TO ME, MAN.
SERIOUSLY, I'LL TAKE IT.
REALLY?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I REALLY-- I'M KIND OF
THINKING I SHOULD GO TO
REDEMPTION.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, COCHRAN?
IT'SA-- YOU KNOW, I AGREE THE
WITH THE PEOPLE THAT SAY IT
SHOULD BE ME.
I DON'T HAVE AS MUCH CONFIDENCE
THEY WILL DO WELL.
OZZY COMES WALTZING INTO THE
CAMP WITH THIS PEARLY NECKLACE
AROUND HIS NECK SAYING VOTE ME
OUT.
SEND ME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IT WAS LIKE THE GOSPEL.
I COULD HAVE DIED RIGHT THERE.
WHAT MAXES YOU THINK THIS?
I JUST THINK THAT I'VE GOT
BETTER ODDS.
I DON'T THINK SO, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW.
THE REACTION TO OZZY
ANNOUNCING THAT HE WOULD BE
WILLING TO GO TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND WAS MET WITH SOME
OPPOSITION, SO I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
AND IT'S CREEPING ME OUT.
MY PIECE WITH IT IS I THINK
EVERYONE SHOULD STAND UP FOR
THEIR OWN ACTIONS AND THAT'S
WHAT I DO IN LIFE AND THAT'S THE
REASON I'M DISAPPOINTED WITH IT.
OZZY IS TALKING ABOUT GOING
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
EYE WON'T AGREE WITH IT.
WHAT WORRIES ME MOST ABOUT THE
PLAN IS THAT THE MERGE IS NOT
GOING TO HAPPEN LIKE WE THINK IT
IS.
WE ARE ONLY AS STRONG AS OUR
WEAKEST LINK, AND THAT'S
COCHRAN.
SO COCHRAN'S LEFT TO BASICALLY
PULL THE REST OF THE WEIGHT THAT
OZZY LEFT BEHIND, AND I DON'T
REALLY KNOW HOW MUCH HOPE WE
HAVE FOR ANOTHER TEAM CHALLENGE.
AND I KNOW KEITH DOESN'T LIKE
THIS IDEA.
I UNDERSTAND WHAT KEITH'S
SAYING.
AND I FEEL THAT WAY VERY
STRONGLY AS WELL.
IF WE'RE WRONG ABOUT THEIR
BEING A MERGE AFTER THE NEXT
REDEMPTION ISLAND, THE BIGGEST
DEAL WOULD BE IF WE HAVE ANOTHER
CHALLENGE AND WE'RE DOWN OZZY
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, DAWN'S OUR
THIRD GUY, COCHRAN WOULD BE OUR
FOURTH GUY.
SCARY POSITION TO BE IN.
Jeff: SO, OZZY, AT THE END
OF THE HALF THE CHALLENGE, THERE
WAS A LOT OF EMOTION.
WAS THERE ANY FINGER POINTING
WHEN YOU GOT BACK TO CAMP?
( LAUGHS ).
YEAH, THERE WAS A LOT OF
EMOTION, AND A LOT OF FINGER
POINTING, MOST OF THE FINGERS
WENT TO COCHRAN.
Jeff: COCHRAN, WHAT
HAPPENED?
I MEAN, I RECOGNIZED THERE
WAS A PROBLEM WHEN DAWN AND
KEITH RETURNED AND THE ROPE WAS
ALL TANGLED UP AND THAT'S WHEN I
STARTED TO PANIC BECAUSE I
WASN'T SURE HOW TO DEAL WITH IT
IN A FAST WAY.
I REMEMBER LOOKING UP AT JIM,
AND JUST BEING BLANK.
, THINKING, GOD, THIS IS MY
WORST NIGHTMARE.
IT WAS EMBARRASSING.
Jeff: SO, JIM, YOU SAW
COCHRAN PANICKING.
COCHRAN HAD GOTTEN TO A POINT
OF FRUSTRATION BECAUSE THE TWO
WERE TANGLED UP AND HE HAD KIND
OF THROWN HIS HANDS UP IN-- THIS
WAS THE LOOK THAT I HAD GOTTEN.
Jeff: COCHRAN, HAVE YOU
FOUND YOURSELF IN SITUATIONS
LIKE THIS WHERE YOU'RE MAYBE OUT
OF YOUR COMFORT ZONE AND THE
PANIC SETS IN?
I'M USUALLY PRETTY CALM, COOL,
AND COLLECTED.
THIS WAS A NEW EXPERIENCE FOR
ME.
IT WAS A HEARTBREAKING
EXPERIENCE FOR ME BECAUSE IT'S A
WELL FOUND BELIEF THAT WE'RE
GOING TO MERGE TOMORROW.
IT'S MIXED EMOTIONS IN THAT
WE'RE GOING TO BE GOING DOWN IN
NUMBER BUT WE'RE HOPING
REDEMPTION ISLAND CAN WORK IN
OUR FAVOR IN SOME WAY AND GET
THE NUMBERS BACK UP TO 6-6.
Jeff: DAWN, COCHRAN SAYS WE
HOPE SOMEHOW REDEMPTION ISLAND
WILL HELP US.
TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
WELL, OUR HOPE IS THAT
WHOEVER GOES TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND CAN WIN THAT DUEL AND
SEND HOME CHRISTINE AND RE-ENTER
THE GAME, AND THEN THAT LEAVES
US SIX UPOLU AND SIX SAVAII
TRIBE MEMBERS.
Jeff: SO, OZZY, YOUR PLAN
IS WHOEVER WE VOTE OUT TONIGHT
SHOULD GO TO REDEMPTION, TRY TO
WIN, COME BACK AND REJOIN US.
YEAH.
Jeff: I'M A LITTLE CONFUSED
BECAUSE WHAT I HEAR YOU SAYING
ON ONE HAND, COCHRAN, COCHRAN,
COCHRAN, COCHRAN, COX RAN?
YEAH.
Jeff: WHY IS HE GOING TO
PUT HIS LIFE ON THE LINE IF YOU
VOTE HIM OUT?
OF COURSE.
THE THING ABOUT IT IS, JEFF, I'M
PUTTING MY LIFE ON THE LINE.
Jeff: YOU'RE PUTTING YOUR
LIFE ON THE LINE.
YES.
Jeff: YOU'RE SAYING YOU'RE
GOING TO GO TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
YES.
YOU CAN BASICALLY SAY I HAD A
DREAM.
I SAW THE MERGE.
AND I SAW MY CHANCE AT MY OWN
REDEMPTION, WHICH HAS BEEN
HAUNTING ME SINCE THE LAST TIME
I PLAYED.
AND THAT'S BY NOT PLAYING THE
IDOL, BY NOT LISTENING TO MY
SENSES AND NOT LISTENING TO MY
HEART AND MY GUT.
AND THIS TIME MY HEART AND MY
GUT IS SAYING GET YOUR ASS TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND AND PROVE TO
YOUR TRIBE THAT YOU ARE WORTH
KEEPING IN THIS GAME.
THIS IS MY OPPORTUNITY TO NOT
ONLY MAKE THE BALLSIEST MOVE I
COULD POSSIBLY THINK OF, BUT TO
PLAY THE BIGGEST, CRAZIEST GAME
I WANT TO PLAY, AND NOT ONLY DO
I HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY BUT I HAD
THE IDOL.
Jeff: YOU HAVE THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL?
YEAH.
Jeff: AND THIS ISN'T NEWS
TO ANYBODY.
SO WHAT DO YOU DO WITH THE IDOL?
I GIVE THE IDOL UP.
AND THIS IS THE PART WHERE IT
GETS INTERESTING.
I'M GOING TO MAKE UP A STORY.
I'M GOING TO TELL CHRISTINE,
THAT COCHRAN, THE LITTLE SMART
WEASEL HE IS THAT HAS BEEN TO
HARVARD LAW AND WATCHES THE GAME
RELIGIOUSLY, FOUND THE IDOL,
KEPT IT FROM US, WE GO TO VOTE
HIM OUT, HE WHIPS OUT THE IDOL,
SEE YOU LATER, OZZY.
NOT ONLY IS COCHRAN THE VILLAIN,
BUT HE'S NOW THE DOUBLE AGENT.
SO I THINK THAT THAT GIVES US
THE BEST SHOT AT TAKING THEM BY
SURPRISE AND POSSIBLY GETTING IN
FRONT OF THIS GAME.
Jeff: WHAT IF WE DON'T
MERGE TOMORROW?
THERE IS A POSSIBILITY THAT
WE DON'T MERGE.
AND THAT THESE GUYS GO TO
ANOTHER CHALLENGE WITHOUT ME.
BUT AT LEAST I'VE GONE OUT ON MY
TERMS, AND I HAVEN'T GONE OUT ON
SOMEONE ELSE'S TERMS LIKE LAST
TIME.
Jeff: LET ME OFFER ANOTHER
ARGUMENT.
IF YOU DON'T WIN THE DUEL
TOMORROW, YOU GO OUT A BIGGER
FOOL THAN YOU DID LAST TIME.
YEAH.
Jeff: KEITH, ANY
RESERVATIONS AT ALL ABOUT THIS?
I THINK I MIGHT HAVE BEEN THE
MOST VOCAL.
I THINK THIS IS COCHRAN'S TIME
TO REDEEM HIMSELF.
AND IT'S HIS CHANCE TO KIND OF
PROVE HIS WORTH TO THE TRIBE.
Jeff: WHITNEY, WHAT'S YOUR
TAKE ON THIS?
YOU KNOW, OZZY'S ONE OF OUR
STRONGEST PLAYERS.
IF WE DO HAVE ANOTHER CHALLENGE
BEFORE THE MERGE HAPPENS, WE'RE
NOT AT OUR 100% WITHOUT OZZY.
Jeff: JIM, WORST THING THAT
HAPPENS TOMORROW MORNING WHEN
YOU WAKE UP?
OZZY LOSES AND WE HAVE TO GO,
THE FIVE OF US STRONG, AGAINST
THE SIX OF THEM.
Jeff: WELL, IT IS
DEFINITELY A RISKY MOVE.
LET'S SEE IF YOU HAVE THE
COURAGE TO GO THROUGH WITH IT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KEITH, YOU'RE UP.
22 SEASONS OF "SURVIVOR" I'VE
NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE THIS,
AND I'M THRILLED TO BE A PART OF
IT, ESPECIALLY IF IT MEANS
SAVING MY ASS FOR ONE MORE TIME
THANK YOU.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL THAT YOU WANT TO
PLAY OR GIVE TO SOMEONE ELSE,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
UHM, I THINK I CHANGED MY
MIND.
I THINK I'M GOING TO LET COCHRAN
GO TO REDEMPTION.
JUST KIDDING.
YOU'RE A BASTARD, MAN.
HOLD ON TO IT, AND--
IT'S GOING TO BE YOURS.
YOU BETTER GIVE THAT TO ME.
IT'S RIGHT BACK AT YOU.
LET'S DO THIS.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE
VOTES ARE READ THE DECISION IS
FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
THE FIRST VOTE, OZZY.
TWO VOTES OZZY.
OZZY.
THREE VOTES OZZY.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC."
LUCKY SEVEN.
Jeff: OZZY, YOU NEED TO
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
GLADLY.
SEE YOU TOMORROW, MAN.
YOU CAN DO IT, MAN.
YEAH, YOU CAN DO IT.
Jeff: OZZY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
Y YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
Jeff: GRAB YOUR TORCH HEAD
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
SLEEP WELL.
BE RIGHT BACK.
Jeff: WELL, YOU JUST MADE
ONE OF THE BIGGEST MOVES IN THE
HISTORY OF THIS GAME BASED ON
ONE BIG ASSUMPTION.
THAT THE MERGE IS NEXT.
YOU'LL FIND OUT SOON ENOUGH IF
YOU WERE RIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": WITH THE POTENTIAL
MERGE ON THE HORIZON, FOR OZZY'S
PLAN TO WORK HE HAS TO WIN AT
REDEMPTION.
IT IS HANGING ON BY THE EDGE OF
THE POLE.
AND COCHRAN HAS TO STAY LOYAL.
FIRST YOU GET THE EGO MANIAC
VOTED OUT.
THEN YOU GET HIS IDOL.
THEN YOU GET THE MILLION
DOLLARS.
HELLO, HELLO.
WHO IS IT?
THE MOVE TO GET MYSELF VOTED
OUT IS PROBABLY EITHER THE
STUPIDEST THING I COULD HAVE
DONE OR IT'S ONE OF THE MOST
ICONIC MOVES IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
SO LAME.
GUESS.
COCHRAN.
YES!