PREVIOUSLY ON "SURVIVOR."
Jeff: IMMUNITY TEAM FOR 19
DAYSTWO SIDES UPOLU AND SAVAII
TRADED VICTORIES IN ONE OF THE
CLOSEST BATTLES EVER WHEN THEY
MERGED IT WAS STILL.
IT'S SIX ON SIX. EVERYBODY
IS LOOKING FOR AN IN.
Jeff: BUT AFTER THE FIRSTTRIBAL
COUNCIL COCHRAN BETRAYED
HIS OWN TRIBE GIVING OLD UPOLU
A
NUMBERS ADVANTAGE.
HE THREW THE WHOLE TRIBE
UNDER THE BUS.
YOU DISGUST ME.
Jeff: JIM, FACING
TONIGHT'STRIBAL COUNCIL -- WHEN
OZZIE
FAILED TO WIN IMMUNITY THEY
JUMPED TO VOTE HIM OUT.
OZZIE ONCE AGAIN.
Jeff: SENDING HIM TOREDEMPTION
ISLAND.
I'M GOING TO TREAT THEM
REALLY NICE THEN SEND THEM
PACKING.
Jeff: AT THE
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE WHITNEY
FROM THE
OLD SAVAII HUNG ON FOR THE WIN.
SHE'S SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
Jeff: BACK AT CAMP
ATER PREVIOUSLY GOING AGAINST
HIS
ALLIANCE AND TARGETING EDNA
ALBERT AGAIN TRIED TO TAKE
CONTROL BY TARGETING JOHN.
I'M THINKING HE'S GOING.
ALBERT IS GETTING NERVOUS.
HE'S THINKING A LOT RIGHT NOW.
BUT IN TRIBAL COUNCIL
ALBERT'S PLAN WAS REJECTED BY
COACH AND THE OLD UPOLU TRIBE.
JIM, TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
JIM WAS SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
NOW WITH SEVEN REMAINING IN THE
UPOLU ALLIANCE THE QUESTION IS,
WILL ANYONE SEIZE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO TEAM UP WITH
DAWN
AND WHITNEY AND TURN THE GAME
UPSIDE DOWN.
WHITNEY WON IMMUNE TIE
TODAY.
THEY ALL SAT OUT.
ALL SEVEN SAT OUT.
AND THEY GAVE THE WHOLE -- WITH
HONOR AND LIKE GETTING.
THE LONGER THAT COACH HAS
THEM BELIEVING THAT THEY'RE ALL
ONE TRIBE MORE LIKELY IT IS
THAT
HE WINS A MILLION DOLLARS.
GOING TO BRING HIM TO THE
END.
PISSES ME OFF.
I HATE TO SAY I TOLD YOU SO.
I WON'T SAY IT.
I.
JIM IS THE MOST DANGEROUS
KIND OF PERSON BECAUSE TO YOUR
FACE AND ON THE SURFACE HE
LOOKS
LIKE THE BEST FRIEND OF
EVERYBODY.
WHEN THE CHIPS ARE DOWN HE
WOULDN'T DO IT -- THAT'S THE
WORST KIND OF GUY.
NOW THAT HE'S GONE WE'RE GOING
TO GROW AS A FAMILY EVEN MORE
SO.
YOU GUYS DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
WORRY ABOUT.
TRUST ME.
SURVIVAL 101, RULE 37, ANYBODY
THAT IS ON THE BOTTOM OF THE
ALLIANCE BETTER NOT FEEL LIKE
THEY'RE ON THE BOTTOM OR
THEY'RE
GOING TO REVOLVE AND SCRAMBLE
TO
FIND A BET ARE PLACE.
I KEEP TALKING TO PEOPLE ABOUT
UNITY AND RESPECT.
BECAUSE PEOPLE GET SCARED IN
THIS GAME.
BLIND SIDES HAPPEN EVERY DAY,
IN
FACT MORE BLIND SIDES HAPPEN
THAN ALLIANCES STICKING
TOGETHER.
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN AROUND ME.
I DON'T DICTATE ANYTHING.
I NEVER TELL THESE GUYS WHO TO
DO.
WE ALL MAKE SUGGESTIONS, IT'S
EQUAL.
COACH IS RUNNING THE SHOW
LIKE HE'S JESUS.
ALL OF THEM THINK THAT THEY'RE
GOING TO GO TO THE END,
OBVIOUSLY SEVEN CAN'T GO TO THE
END.
IT'S SO FRUSTRATING I KIND OF
WANT TO LAUGH AT HIM BE LIKE,
Y'ALL ARE SO SMART, COCHRAN
WENT
TO HARVARD.
SOPHIE IS GOING TO MED SCHOOL.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW THESE
SMART PEOPLE CAN BE SO STUPID.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
♪♪
45 DEGREE ANGLE.
STEP OUT.
AND PUSH THAT TARGET OUT.
COME BACK LIKE YOU'RE SHOOTING
A
BOW.
PEOPLE IT AS YOU PULL BACK THEN
WE'LL COME OUT OF IT. YOU CAN
COME OUT OF IT ANY WAY YOU WANT
TO.
COME BACK TO THE CENTER.
BRING YOUR HANDS TOGETHER.
AS PAINFUL AS IT IS TO ADMIT
IT, I AM DRINKING THE COACH'S
KOOL-AID, NOT IN HUGE GULPS BUT
TAKING GINGER STEPS.
I'M GOING TO MEET MY UNTIMELY
DEATH, I GOT TO OBEY THE FATHER
OF THE FAMILY.
I GOT TO TELL YOU, MAN, I'M
A LITTLE BIT WORRIED.
I'M A LITTLE BIT WORRIED.
ABOUT WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST WORRIED, MAN.
ALBERT'S BEEN REALLY SQUIRRELY
THE LAST COUPLE OF DAYS.
BRANDON'S RUNNING AROUND IN
BRANDON MODE.
SOMETIMES THINK I'M GOING TO
GET
BLINDSIDED.
DO YOU THINK EVERYBODY ELSE
IS GOING TO VOTE?
I WILL DO EVERYTHING IN MY
POWER TO MAKE SURE THAT DOESN'T
HAPPEN.
BUT EVERYBODY ALWAYS SAYS THAT
I'M IN CONTROL OF THE GAME, I'M
REALLY NOT.
I THINK YOU'RE WORRIED THAT
ALBERT IS GOING TO DO
SOMETHING.
I JUST THINK THAT FISHY
THINGS ARE ABROAD.
KIND OF ALARMING TO HEAR
THAT COACH IS CONCERNED ABOUT
ALBERT IN THE GAME RIGHT NOW.
SOME SORT OF POWER STRUGGLE,
ALBERT HE'S POSSIBLY ONE OF THE
TWO BIGGEST LEADERS OF THAT
GROUP SO IT'S POSSIBLE HE'S
AWARE THAT THEY ARE GUNNING FOR
HIM EARLIER THAN THEY SAY THEY
ARE.
SO I'M STARTING TO GET
CONCERNED
ABOUT MY PLACE.
I FELT COMFORTABLE 24 HOURS
AGO,
TODAY I'M NOT SO COMFORTABLE.
Jeff: NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUAL.
KEITH, OZZIE AND JIM VOTED OUT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BROUGHT THE WHOLE TRIBE HERE TO
WITNESS TODAY'S DUAL.
HERE IS HOW IT WORKS.
WITH YOUR ARMS OUTSTRETCHED YOU
WILL USE THE TOP OF YOUR HAND
TOEHOLD TWO POLES AGAINST AN
OVERHEAD BOARD.
IF YOU LOWER YOUR HANDS EVEN
SLIGHTLY THE POLES WILL DROP,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE DUEL.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING STAYS
ALIVE IN THIS DUEL WITH A SHOT
AT A MILLION DOLLARS.
THE TWO LOSERS ARE OUT FOR GOOD
AND WILL BECOME THE FIRST AND
SECOND MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
OH, WOW.
Jeff: BIG STAKES.THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT, TAKE YOUR SPOT.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY IS IN POSITION.
THIS DUEL IS ON.
THIS IS ANOTHER DUEL WHERE YOU
NEED TO CONCENTRATE.
BECAUSE IF YOU LOWER YOUR HANDS
EVEN JUST A LITTLE BIT, THAT'S
ALL THAT POLE NEEDS TO FALL TO
THE SIDE.
FIRST PERSON OUT BECOMES THE
FIRST MEMBER OF THE JURY.
SECOND PERSON OUT BECOMES
SECOND
MEMBER OF THE JURY.
LAST PERSON STANDING IS STILL
IN
THE HUNT FOR A MILLION DOLLARS.
HUGE STAKES AT THIS DUEL.
Jeff: WHO ARE YOU ROOTING
FORBRANDON?
I'D LOOK TO ROOT FOR JIM.
Jeff: ANYBODY HERE ROOTINGFOR
KEITH?
YES.
GO KEITH.
Jeff: HOW ABOUT FOR OZZY?OZZY
IS ON HIS OWN.
JIM DROPS OUT OF THE DUEL.
JIM BECOMES THE FIRST MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
WE'RE DOWN TO OZZY AND KEITH.
THEY WERE TRIBE MATES AT ONE
POINT NOW THEY'RE BATTLING
AGAINST EACH OTHER, ONE STAYS
ALIVE.
ONE JOINS THE JURY.
KEITH GETTING CLOSE TO THAT
EDGE.
OZZY WITH A BIT OF MOVEMENT.
STAY FOCUSED.
IF YOU WANT TO WIN THIS GAME
YOU
HAVE TO WIN THIS DUEL.
THAT IS IT.
IT COULDN'T BE ANY MORE CLEAR.
BOTH GUYS WITH THEIR POLES ON
THE EDGE OF THEIR BOARDS.
OZZY FLIRTING WITH DISASTER
TRYING TO KEEP HIS POLE ON THE
BOARD.
TINIEST LITTLE MOVEMENT THOSE
POLES ARE GOING TO DROP.
KEITH DROPS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
KEITH BECOMES THE SECOND MEMBER
OF OUR JURY.
OZZY STAYS ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
AND REMAINS A THREAT TO GET
BACK
IN.
OZZY, THE ONE GUY WHO HAD NO
SUPPORT FROM THE TRIBE.
I'M SITTING IN THE BEST PLACE
I THINK THAT I COULD.
HOW SO?
I DON'T HAVE TO RELY ON
PEOPLE'S TRUST I'M SITTING
THERE
AT REDEMPTION EATING MY HEART
OUT, GETTING READY FOR THE NEXT
PERSON TO COME IN.
I'LL BE NICE, I'LL MAKE FISH,
MAKE YOU FRUIT.
THEN COME IN I'LL BEAT YOU,
I'LL
BE SITTING AT THE END, TOO, SEE
WHO IS BACK STABBED WHO AND WHO
IS TAKEN THE HIGHER ROAD, IF
YOU
WILL.
HUGE FAN OF "SURVIVOR ."
BIG FAN.
Jeff: WANTED TO BE PART OFTHIS
EXPERIENCE FOR A LONG TIME.
I'M HOPING THERE'S A SECRET
DOUBLE REDEMPTION ISLAND.
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
Jeff: THERE IS NO
DOUBLE REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU'LL BECOME FIRST MEMBER OF
OUR JURY TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
[ Applause ]
THIS ADVENTURE IS OVER, YOU'LL
BECOME THE SECOND MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
GOOD JOB, KEITH.
GOOD PLUCK.
OZZY, STAY ALIVE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK, AWAIT YOUR NEXT DUEL.
SEE YOU LATER GUYS.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I GOT TO SAY BEING ALONE ON
REDEMPTION IS A BEAUTIFUL
THING.
I'VE REALLY SCORED OUT HERE.
LIKE MY MINI PARADISE.
I'VE GOT ALL THAT I COULD EVER
WANT IN FOOD.
ONE OF THE MOST BEAUTIFUL REEFS
FULL OF CAVS.
I'M REALLY GLAD THAT TE TUNA
TRIBE IS MISSING MY SKILLS.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL NOBODY IS
ABLE TO GET OUT THERE AND GO
FISHING.
BECAUSE THEY GOT TO SPEND A LOT
OF THEIR ENERGY WATCHING OUT,
WHO IS DOING WHAT AND WHERE
PEOPLE ARE GOING AND WHO PEOPLE
ARE TALKING TO.
THEY GOT TO WATCH OUT FOR THE
COULD NOTIFYING NATURE THAT IS
THE NORMAL CLASSIC END GAME OF
"SURVIVOR".
REDEMPTION ADDS A WHOLE NEW
TWIST.
YOU HAVE THE SKILLS AND ABILITY
LIKE I DO, YOU CAN COME OUT
HERE
AND REALLY REFRESH, REJUVENATE
GET EVERYTHING SET TO GO AND
PLAY THE END GAME WITH A
PASSION
AND A FEROCITY THAT YOU CAN'T
GET WHEN YOU'RE HAVING TO DEAL
WITH A TRIBE.
I THINK IT'S THAT DUEL PROVES
THAT I'M A HUGE PHYSICAL THREAT
STILL.
AND IF ANYTHING I'VE JUST
GOTTEN
STRONGER SINCE BEING OUT HERE
ON
REDEMPTION.
AND THE NEXT COUPLE PEOPLE
COMING THROUGH REDEMPTION ARE
GOING TO HAVE A BIG CHALLENGE
IN
FRONT OF THEM.
AND THAT'S ME.
NOTHING, HUH?
I JEOPARDIZED MY OWN GAME
AND DIDN'T OUT YOUR GAME PLAN.
WHEN OUR GROUP COULD HAVE SHOOK
IT UP.
I FEEL LIKE YOU COULD
RECIPROCATE.
I'LL DO ANYTHING TO STAY IN
NOW.
YOU'RE STILL THE NUMBER ONE
PERSON ON THE LIST.
THERE'S SOMETHING APPEALING
ABOUT THE IDEA OF RETURNING TO
DAWN AND WHITNEY.
THEY KNOW IT'S GOING TO
BASICALLY HAVE TO BE THE ACT OF
AN ANGEL LOOKING OVER THEM TO
CARRY THEM FURTHER.
I THINK IF I WERE THAT ANGEL
THAT WOULD PROBABLY EARN ME A
LOT MORE JURY VOTES THAN JUST
BLINDLY FOLLOWING THE UPOLU.
I'M WILLING TO CHANGE --
YEAH.
I GET IT.
EITHER WAY IT'S GOING TO BE
A LEAP OF FAITH.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TRUST THAT
THE FEW PROMISES I HAVE
RECEIVED
TO TAKE ME FURTHER THAN 7th
PLACE HAVE BEEN SINCERE OR IF I
REALLY AM 7th IN LINE I GOT
MAKE A BIG MOVE.
THIS IS SOMETHING I NEED TO
SERIOUSLY CONSIDER.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT GUYS READY TO GET TO
YOUR IMMUNE FECAL THEN FIRST
THINGS FIRST, WHITNEY, I HAVE
TO
TAKE IT BACK.
NOT GOING TO HELP ME AT ALL,
ARE
YOU?
NOPE.
I DON'T WANT TO LET GO OF IT.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY,
BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
BALANCE A BOWL FILLED WITH RICE
ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD.
ON MY GO YOU WILL RACE ACROSS
TWO TEETER-TOTTERS AND EMPTY
YOUR RICE IN TO A CONTAINER.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU TOUCH THE
BOWL WHILE ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD
OR THE BOWL FALLS OFF YOU GOT
TO
GO BACK TO THE START.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY.
IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE AND IS
ONE
STEP CLOSER TO THE MONEY.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL DRAW FOR
SPOTS,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY.
PUT YOUR BOWLS ON TOP OF YOUR
HEAD.
FIND A GOOD SWEET SPOT, GET
THAT
BEANBAG ON THERE, MAKE SURE
BOWL FEELS COMFORTABLE.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO FOR
IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY.
GO!
MAKING SURE YOU GET A GOOD FIT
ON YOUR HEAD IS KEY.
ALBERT BACK TO THE START.
COACH HAS TO HEAD BACK.
COCHRAN'S GOT TO HEAD BACK.
LOT OF BALANCE IN THIS.
USE YOUR BODY.
RICK HANGING ON THERE.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
DAWN OFF TO A GOOD START.
DAWN ALMOST LOSES IT, NICE
RECOVERY.
BRANDON AND SOPHIE TRYING TO
WIN
THIS.
DAWN IS BACK.
SHE EMPTIED HER RICE.
BRANDON'S BACK WITH HIS RICE.
SOPHIE BACK WITH HER RICE.
WE GOT A CHALLENGE NOW.
COACH GIVING IT ANOTHER SHOT.
COACH GOT SOMETHING GOING NOW.
WHITNEY UP AND OVER THAT FIRST
TEETER TOTTER HEADING OUT ON
THE
SECOND.
ONCE YOU FIND THAT SWEET SPOT
THIS GETS EASIER.
GOT TO HEAD BACK.
COACH WITH HIS BOWL OF RICE.
WHITNEY, CLOSE, WHITNEY FALLS.
BRANDON AND EDNA DOING GREAT.
EDNA ALMOST.
FALLS OUT, EDNA HAS TO HEAD
BACK.
BRANDON WITH HIS SECOND BOWL OF
RICE.
DAWN NOT MESSING AROUND, SHE
KNOWS SHE NEEDS IMMUNITY
TONIGHT.
DAWN WITH ANOTHER BOWL OF RICE.
SOPHIE WITH ANOTHER BOWL OF
RICE.
BRANDON, DAWN AND SOPHIE
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
EVERYBODY ELSE STRUGGLING.
IT HAS COME DOWN TO A
THREE-PERSON CHALLENGE RIGHT
NOW.
IT IS DAWN, BRANDON AND SOPHIE.
SOPHIE NOW WITH A HUGE MOVE, A
VERY FULL BOWL OF RICE.
IT IS OVERFLOWING.
SOPHIE HAS MORE RICIN HER BOWL
THAN ANYBODY ELSE HAS TAKEN AT
ONE TIME.
THAT THING IS FILLED TO THE
BRIM.
THAT COULD BE ENOUGH.
BRANDON WITH ANOTHER BOWL OF
RICE.
WILL THAT DO IT?
NO.
DAWN WITH ANOTHER BOWL OF RICE.
SHE'S CLOSE.
SOPHIE, WILL IT BE ENOUGH RICE?
SOPHIE WITH THAT WINS IMMUNITY!
WOW!
SOPHIE, COME ON OVER.
[ Applause ]
GOOD JOB, SOPHIE.
SO PROUD OF YOU.
NICE JOB.
Jeff: SOPHIE IS SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ONE STEP CLOSER TO GETTING TO
THE END.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, TONIGHT A
TWIST
OF TRIBAL COUNCIL WHICH WILL BE
REVEALED AT TRIBAL.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
WHITNEY AND I ARE ON THE
OUT.
WE HAD TO WIN THE CHALLENGE FOR
SURE.
BUT I HAVEN'T LOST HOPE.
JEFF SAID TRIBAL COUNCIL THERE
WILL BE A TWIST.
SO I THINK IF THIS ISN'T THE
TIME TO GET UP BECAUSE ANYTHING
CAN HAPPEN.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
I WAS DISAPPOINTED WITH MY
PERFORMANCE IN TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, I THOUGHT THERE WAS
A
CHANCE I WOULD EXCEL.
AGAIN MY LACK OF BALANCE AND
AGILITY CAME BACK TO HAUNT ME.
IT WAS DEFINITELY DAWN AND
WHITNEY.
THING IS THAT IF DAWN GETS TO
THE END OF THIS GAME SHE'LL
WIN.
NO QUESTION.
THAT'S WHY WE WANT TO GET
HER OFF SOONER THAN LATER.
LUCKILY DAWN AND WHITNEY ARE IN
SUCH A BAD POSITION RIGHT NOW.
THEY KNOW THEY'RE THE NEXT TWO
TO GO.
UNFORTUNATELY WHEN JEFF
MENTIONED THERE WOULD BE A
TWIST
AT TONAL'S TRIBAL COUNCIL MY
FIRST THOUGHT, DOUBLE
ELIMINATION.
THERE'S ALWAYS THE POSSIBILITY
THAT AFTER WE VOTE OUT ONE OF
THE TWO THERE WILL BE ANOTHER
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IF ONE OF
THE
REMANNING TWO WINS THAT
CHALLENGE, I COULD BE IN
DANGER.
SO I'M A LITTLE BIT NERVOUS.
WE NEEDED TO WIN THAT.
SO MAD AT MYSELF.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE ME.
I HAD TO WIN THE CHALLENGE
TODAY, THERE WASN'T ANY WAY
AROUND IT.
I'M MOST LIKELY GOING TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND TONIGHT.
THEY ARE SO ISSUE ABOUT THE --
COACH HAS THIS LOYAL FOLLOWING.
BUT IT'S NOT OVER.
I MEAN THE ONE THING ABOUT THIS
GAME IS YOU CAN LAY IN BED AND
THINK, I'M GOING HOME.
AND WHOLE DAY CHANGES.
THAT'S OUR ONLY HOPE.
RIGHT NOW WE'D BE UP FOR
MAKING A MOVE.
JUST PICKING THE RIGHT PEOPLE,
BRANDON IS SUCH A LOOSE CANNON
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
BELIEVE.
RICK, HE'S NOT EVEN PLAYING
THE GAME.
EDNA, SHE'S SO FAR UP COACH'S
BUTT IT'S RIDICULOUS.
ALBERT AT LEAST SEEMS LIKE A
GOOD GUY.
WE'RE TWO VOTES THAT CAN
HELP SOMEONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHO IT IS.
WE HAVE NO ALLIANCE TO
ANYONE.
RIGHT NOW I'M AT A
CROSSROADS.
I FEEL LIKE MY ONLY REAL CHANCE
TO WIN THIS GAME IS TO SECURE
EVERY SAVAII VOTE.
I HAVE POSSIBLY GETTING EDNA
IMMEDIATELY FOR COUPLE OF
REASONS.
A, I REALLY WANT TO CREDIT
COCHRAN FOR WHAT HE'S DONE FOR
US BY MOVING HIM UP THE LADDER,
SO TO SPEAK.
ALSO WANT TO CURRY A LITTLE BIT
OF EXTRA FAVOR WITH A WHITNEY
OR
DAWN.
NOW I'VE BUTTERED THREE
POTENTIAL JURY MEMBERS AND LOST
AN EDNA WHO WASN'T GOING TO
VOTE
FOR ME ANYWAY.
LIKE EDNA HAS NOT DONE A
THING.
BASICALLY JUST BEEN FOLLOWING
COAT TAILS AND FOLLOWS HIM
AROUND.
LIKE TO ME THAT'S BOGUS,
BECAUSE
I HOPsLY TRULY LEGITIMATELY
FEEL THAT YOU GUYS DESERVE IT
MORE.
COCHRAN AND MYSELF PLUS YOU AND
DAWN AND ONE MORE PERSON THAT
WOULD BE FIVE.
AND VOTE EDNA.
THANK YOU.
I AM IN WITH THAT.
I'M ON BOARD.
A BIZARRE THING NOT TO TALK
TO THESE PEOPLE.
NOT TO BE RUDE BUT WHEN TIMES
COME TO VOTE SOMEONE OUT YOU
CAN'T SIT THERE MAKE YOURSELF
AVAILABLE.
I DIDN'T SEE THAT.
I'M SCREWED.
BIG TIME.
ALBERT JUST CONFIRMED MY
SUSPICION, IS THAT I'M GOING TO
BE VOTED OUT.
NOT EXACTLY SHOCKED BUT I FELT
COMPLETE BETRAYAL OF OUR TRUST
BECAUSE I SAVED THAT ENTIRE
TRIBE.
IF THEY THINK THAT EDNA IS A
MORE VALUABLE PLAYER FOR THEM
SOMEBODY WHO MADE MORE
SACRIFICES FOR THEM THEY'RE
SORELY MISTAKEN.
I CAME TO PLAY "SURVIVOR"
IT'S ABOUT BIG MOVES.
I DIDN'T MAKE THE BIG JUMP I
DID
TO BE VOTED OUT.
I WANTED TO MOVE FURTHER IN
THIS
GAME.
IF THAT MEANS SLIPPING BACK
AGAIN THEN SOMETHING I HAVE TO
CONSIDER.
HOW ARE WE DOING?
DOING GOOD.
I JUST WANT TO TELL WHAT YOU
THE DEAL S. WHITNEY AND DAWN
ARE
OBVIOUSLY DEAD PEOPLE WALKING.
BUT HERE'S THE THING.
WHO IS EDNA GOING TO HAVE THE
MOST ALLEGIANCE TO AS A JURY
MEMBER?
COACH.
WE'RE NEVER GETTING HER
VOTE.
IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS.
WHY DON'T WE TAKE THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO MAKE GOOD OF
WHAT
SOME PEOPLE LIKE A DAWN AND
WHITNEY WHO COULD END UP BEING
VOTES FOR US AT THE END.
I'M GOING TO PUT THE CARDS ON
THE TABLE F. WE DON'T RID OF
EDNA NOW.
ALBERT IS SHOWING HIS TRUE
COLORS MORE AND MORE WHICH ARE
SAME THREE MY TRUE COLORS.
THIS IS OUR ONE SHOT TO MAKE
THE
BIG MOVES.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TWO, THREE
VOTES HANGING AROUND.
I'VE GIVEN NO PROMISES TO EDNA.
THEY ANNOY THE HELL OUT OF ME.
SHE WRINGS IT TO THE TABLE.
NOT OUT ORGANIZE, OUT CLEAN,
OUT
GATHER.
IT'S FRICKIN' SURVIVOR.
ALBERT IS TRYING TO TAKE
CONTROL OF THIS GAME AND I'M
THE
SWING VOTE.
SO NOW I'M DEBATING WHETHER TO
STICK WITH COACH OR GO WITH
ALBERT'S CRAZY PLAN.
IN THE END OF THE DAY IT'S A
QUESTION OF WHAT WILL TAKE ME
TO
THE END.
I THINK COACH IS GETTING
SUSPICIOUS.
THAT WORRIES ME.
ALBERT RIGHT NOW IS PLAYING
FOR ALBERT THAT'S A DANGEROUS
GAME TO PLAY.
SEE HIM TALKING TO WHITNEY,
DAWN, EITHER TRYING TO COME UP
WITH A PLAN OR TRYING TO CURRY
JURY VOTES.
NEITHER ONE IS ACCEPTABLE IN MY
OPINION.
IF ANYBODY WANTS TO GO OVER
FIVE IT'S INSTANT DEATH.
THERE ARE THREE TYPES OF
MOTIVATIONAL STYLE, THERE IS
CODDLING, REAFFIRMING AND FEAR.
SO I FEEL AT THE MOMENT LIKE AN
OLD MOB BOSS.
IF ANYBODY GOES AGAINST THE
FAMILY, THEY'RE DEAD.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
OUR MEMBERS OF THE JURY.
JIM AND KEITH.
SO DAWN, ONCE THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE WAS OVER YOU KNEW YOU
DIDN'T HAVE IMMUNITY YOUR JOB
BECAME, FIND A CRACK OR CREATE
A
CRACK IN THIS ALLIANCE OF
SEVEN.
TELL ME HOW THE AFTERNOON WENT?
I THINK IT'S TIME FOR THEM
TO USE THE TWO OF US.
IT'S HARD, PEOPLE THAT I SEE IN
FIVE, SIX AND SEVEN POSITION
SEEM CONTENT TO STAY WITH THE
GROUP AT FIVE, SIX AND SEVEN.
Jeff: YOUR PITCH IS, FIVE,
SIX AND SEVEN COME WITH WHITNEY
AND ME AND WE'VE GOT FIVE.
RIGHT.
Jeff: WE'VE WE'RE NOW THE
FINAL FIVE.
RIGHT.
Jeff: WHITNEY, WHO HAVE
YOU HEARD IS FIVE, SIX AND
SEVEN?
COCHRAN IS SEVEN THAT'S ALL
I KNOW.
Jeff: YOU FEEL CONFIDENT
ABOUT THAT?
I DO.
Jeff: BASED ON WHAT?
JUST OBSERVATION AND JUST
HEARING SOME THINGS.
Jeff: HOW DOES THAT MAKE
YOU FEEL?
NOT THE FIRST TIME THIS TOPIC
HAS COME UP.
I'M AWARE I'M IN POSITION
WHERE I'M A LATE COMER TO THE
UPOLU GROUP BE TEMPTING TO
AUTOMATICALLY MAKE ME SEVEN
BECAUSE OF THAT.
I'M CONFIDENT THAT IF I DO
REACH
THAT POSITION I'LL BE ABLE TO
DO
SOME MANEUVERING.
Jeff: YOU'RE TELLING ME AS
AN AVID FAN OF THIS GAME YOU
HAVE NOT STARTED THINKING
BEYOND
SEVEN?
YOU'RE THERE.
THIS IS HAPPENING.
THERE ARE SEVEN AND THERE ARE
TWO.
TONIGHT I'M GUESSING IT'S DAWN
OR WHITNEY WHERE THERE'S A
CRACK
AND SOMEBODY IS ABOUT TO GET
BLINDSIDED.
IF NOT YOU'RE GOING TO BE VERY,
VERY LATE TO A PARTY THAT NOT
GOING TO BE INTERESTED IN
LETTING YOU IN THE DOOR.
I AM PLANNING AHEAD.
I'M SPEAKING IN THE FUTURE
TENSE
I'M ALREADY MAKING PLANS WHAT I
WOULD LIKE TO HAVE HAPPEN.
THERE ARE FRACTURES.
Jeff: LET ME PUT IT TO YOU
DIFFERENT.
TRUE OR FALSE, THIS IS GREAT
TIME FOR SOMEBODY TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE.
THIS IS THE IDEAL TIME TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE.
THERE FOR PEOPLE THAT THEY KNOW
THEY'RE IN A DESPERATE
SITUATION, THEY'RE PROBABLY
WILLING TO DEVOTE THEIR ENTIRE
LOYALTY TO WHOEVER IS WILLING
TO
BRING THEM A LITTLE BIT FURTHER
IN THE GAME.
BUT THIS IS TIME TO MAKE A BIG,
BIG MOVE.
AS A SURVIVOR MAN I LIKE BIG
MOVES.
Jeff: DAWN, WHAT IS YOUR
BEST MOVE?
MY BEST MOVE RIGHT NOW TO
SAY, I'VE GOT NOTHING BUT
LOYALTY.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN HARD
COMPETITOR IN THE GAME I FEEL
LIKE MY WORD HAS BEEN KEPT.
AND IN THE PEOPLE THAT I'VE
SPOKE TO TODAY, YOU KNOW THAT I
ABSOLUTELY WOULD STAND BEHIND
YOU.
Jeff: COACH, HOW
CONCERNING IS THIS TO YOU THAT
ONE PERSON CHANGES THEIR MIND
AND STARTS A SHIFT AND A BIG
MOVE HAPPENS AND SUDDENLY THIS
GAME WHICH IS IN SUCH CONTROL
RIGHT NOW STARTS TO SLIP AWAY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALWAYS A
CONCERN.
I'M ALWAYS THINKING ABOUT IT.
SOMETIMES I SIT AND I WATCH
PEOPLE GO OFF IN TO GROUPS, WE
HAVE THINKERS ON THIS TRIBE.
WHAT HAPPENS IF.
SO CAN THESE TWO GARNER TWO OR
THREE VOTES AND CHANGE THE
ENTIRE GAME.
ABSOLUTELY.
I DON'T DO A LOT OF TALKING
CONTRARY TO POPULAR BELIEVE I'M
NOT RUNNING THIS THIS ALLIANCE
OR RUNNING THE SHOW BUT I'M
ALWAYS THINKING IN THE BACK OF
MY HEAD THAT PEOPLE HAVE TO
MAKE
BIG MOVES IN ORDER TO GET
FURTHER IN THIS GAME.
SO I WORRY, I STRESS, I
BELIEVE,
I TRUST, ALL OF THOSE EMOTIONS
ALL DAY LONG.
IT DRIVES ME CRAZY.
Jeff: WHITNEY.
WHEN COACH SAID CONTRARY TO
POPULAR BEE LEAVE I'M NOT THE
LEADER OF THIS TRIBE YOU KIND
OF
SMILED AND ROLLED YOUR EYES.
DID I?
WELL, I JUST SEE A LOT OF --
JUST OBSERVING THINGS LIKE
EVERYBODY ALWAYS REPORTS BACK
TO
COACH.
SEEMS LIKE MAYBE THAT WOULD BE
THE POSITION HE'S IN THERE.
IF THEY'RE ALWAYS REPORTING
BACK
THAT'S WHAT YOU GOT TO ASSUME,
RIGHT?
Jeff: DOES THAT SURPRISE
THAT YOU SHE OBSERVED THAT
EVERYBODY GOES BACK TO COACH.
NO, DOESN'T SURPRISE ME AT
ALL.
IT'S BEEN WIDELY INTERPRETED
THAT COACH IS LEADER BY A LOT
OF
THE MEMBERS --
Jeff: IS HE YOUR LEADER?
I DON'T THINK HE IS MY
LEADER OR THIS LEADER OF THIS
GROUP OR ALLIANCE MIGHT JUST BE
A FIGUREHEAD WHO REPRESENTS
LEAD
ARE SHIP TO THE GROUP OR MIGHT
BE PULLING THE REAL STRINGS.
IT'S VERY EASY TO MAKE THAT
NATURAL CONNECTION FROM COACH
TO
LEADER.
Jeff: COACH --
I DON'T FEEL LIKE I'M A
LEADER BUT OBVIOUSLY I LIKE TO
HEAR INFORMATION.
KNICKS IS THE BIGGEST POWER IN
THIS GAME.
WHEN PEOPLE GIVE ME INFORMATION
I TAKE IT, I FILE IT AWAY.
I USE IT ONE DAY WHEN I THINK
THAT MY LIFE IS IN JEOPARDY OUT
HERE, WHICH THAT DAY IS COMING,
FAIRLY SOON, YES.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO GET TO THE VOTE.
DAWN AND WHITNEY CLEARLY YOU
TWO
ARE ON THE BUBBLE UNLESS
SOMEBODY IN THIS GROUP OF SEVEN
DECIDES TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE.
SOPHIE HAS IMMUNITY.
EVERYBODY IS FAIR GAME.
BRANDON, YOU'RE UP.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS HIDDEN IMMUNITY
YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW WOULD
BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA
IMMEDIATE LEECH I'LL READ THE
VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, DAWN.
EDNA.
DAWN, TWO VOTES FOR DAWN.
EDNA, WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES DAWN, TWO VOTES EDNA.
DAWN.
THREE VOTES DAWN.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES DAWN TWO,
VOTES EDNA.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
SURVIVOR: SOUTH PARK.
DAWN.
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DAWN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE DONE THAT GET
BACK
IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND, GOOD LUCK.
OKAY, NOW THE TWIST I TOLD YOU
ABOUT EARLIER.
WE'RE GOING TO GO RIGHT IN TO
ANOTHER IMMUNITY CHALLENGE WITH
A VOTE TO FOLLOW.
Jeff: OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO GO RIGHT IN TO
ANOTHER IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
SOPHIE, TAKE THAT IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
FOR GRABS.
I'M NOW GOING TO ASK YOU SERIES
OF SURVIVAL RELATED QUESTIONS.
AFTER 27 DAYS OUT HERE THIS IS
STUFF YOU SHOULD KNOW.
ANSWER CORRECTLY YOU STAY
ALIVE.
YOU GET IT WRONG, YOU'RE OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
GRAB THE CUBE BEHIND YOU.
ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE BEGIN?
FIRST QUESTION, TO PREVENT
DEHYDRATION IT'S RECOMMENDED
THAT SURVIVORS DRINK HOW MUCH
PURIFIED WATER EVERY DAY?
A, ONE PINT.
B, ONE QUART.
C, ONE DPAL LONE.
ONCE YOU HAVE IT HOLD IT IN
FRONT OF YOU.
OKAY.
CORRECT ANSWER IS, C, ONE
GALLON.
WHITNEY GOT IT RIGHT.
COCHRAN GOT IT RIGHT.
COACH GOT IT RIGHT.
BRANDON GOT IT RIGHT.
SOPHIE GOT IT RIGHT.
ALBERT, YOU'RE WRONG.
EDNA, YOU'RE WRONG, RICK,
YOU'RE
WRONG.
SET YOUR CUBES DOWN YOU'RE OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
JUST LIKE THAT WE ARE DOWN TO
FIVE.
NEXT QUESTION.
TRUE OR FALSE: THE COCONUT CRAB
GETS ITS NAME BECAUSE IT'S
FAVORITE FOOD IS COCONUT.
CORRECT ANSWER IS TRUE.
WHITNEY STAYS ALIVE.
COACH STAYS ALIVE.
SOPHIE STAYS ALIVE.
COCHRAN, BRANDON, YOU'RE OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE.
WHITNEY, COACH AND SOPHIE.
THE SOFT EDIBLE FLESH FOUND
INSIDE THE SHELL OF A FALLEN
COCONUT IS CALLED, A, PACIFIC
ARTICHOKE.
B, HEART OF PALM.
C, PALM FINGERS: OR D, COCOA
SPROUTS.
WHITNEY AND SOPHIE BOTH SAY
HEART OF PALM.
COACH SAYS COCOA SPROUT.
COACH, I DON'T KNOW WHAT A
COCOA
SPROUT IS BUT IT'S INCORRECT.
COACH IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WHITNEY AND SOPHIE ARE BOTH
RIGHT.
IT IS HEART OF PALM.
WE'RE NOW DOWN TO WHITNEY AND
SOPHIE.
INTERESTING SITUATION, ISN'T
IT?
THE ONE PERSON CLEARLY IN
TROUBLE TONIGHT IS WHITNEY.
SHE'S ONE OF THE TWO PEOPLE
LEFT
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
TRUE OR FALSE: ALTHOUGH THEY
ARE QUITE DELICIOUS, YOU SHOULD
NOT ATTEMPT TO REMOVE GIANT
SOUTH PACIFIC CLAMS FROM THE
OCEAN AS THEY ARE CONSIDERED
DANGEROUS.
TRUE OR FALSE.
THIS WILL DECIDE IT RIGHT HERE.
WHITNEY SAYS IT IS TRUE.
YOU SHOULD NOT ATTEMPT TO
REMOVE
THEM BECAUSE THEY ARE
DANGEROUS.
SOPHIE SAYS, THAT IS FALSE.
CORRECT ANSWER...
FALSE.
THEY ARE NOT DANGEROUS AT ALL.
SOPHIE WINS ANOTHER IMMUNITY.
WHITNEY, SO CLOSE.
SOPHIE COME ON OVER.
SOPHIE ONCE AGAIN YOU ARE SAFE
FROM THE VOTE.
CANNOT VOTE FOR SOPHIE.
EVERYBODY SELLS FAIR GAME.
SOPHIE, IF YOU'LL TAKE THIS
BACK
AND VOTE FIRST.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, COCHRAN.
WHITNEY.
TWO VOTES WHITNEY.
THREE VOTES WHITNEY.
WHITNEY, THAT'S FOUR VOTES
WHITNEY.
ONE VOTE COCHRAN.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTHABLE PACIFIC"
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
WHITNEY, TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GOOD LUCK.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THE SEVEN
OF YOU HAVE ACCOMPLISHED YOUR
GOAL.
BAD NEWS, NO WHERE LEFT TO
HIDE.
THIS GAME IS ABOUT TO CHANGE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
NEXT TIME ON "SURVIVOR"
BRANDON STOPS CATCHING FISH.
EVERYONE HERE ABSOLUTELY
STARVING.
START CATCHING HEAT.
BRANDON DOESN'T HAVE ANY
BUSINESS IN THIS GAME.
AND UPGRADES HIS NAME.
MY NAME SHOULD BE ZEUS.