Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": WE ARE NECK AND NECK
IN OUR FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE!
FOR THE PAST 17 DAYS, IT'S BEEN
A SEE SAW BATTLE BETWEEN TWO OF
SURVIVOR'S MOST EVENLY MATCHED
TRIBES.
THIS IS HOW CLOSE THIS CHALLENGE
WAS.
ONE COCONUT AWAY.
AT SAVAII, OZZY FOUND A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
SOMETHING GOOD!
Jeff: AND THOUGHT HE WAS IN
CONTROL OF THE DOMINANT
ALLIANCE.
I AM THE ANCHOR.
THEY WANT ME TO TELL THEM HOW TO
DO EVERYTHING.
Jeff: BUT ONE OF HIS
ALLIES, JIM, WAS PLOTTING
AGAINST HIM.
JIM TEAMED UP WITH COCHRAN AND
DAWN TO TARGET OZZY.
IF ELYSE GOES FIRST, THAT
BUYS ME ANOTHER THREE DAYS.
Jeff: AT UPOLU, COACH WAS
SAFE IN HIS ALLIANCE.
I THINK I'M SITTING PRETTY
RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: BUT NOT EVERYONE WAS
A COACH FAN.
I'M NOT BUYING COACH'S BS AT
ALL.
Jeff: STACEY WAS ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK SO SHE LOOKED IN
VAIN FOR THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
TY IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, DAWN
PROVED SHE IS ONE OF THE
COMPETITORS.
DAWN WINS FOR SAVAII!
UPOLU WENT TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE BRANDON, THE NEPHEW OF THE
NOTORIOUS RUSSELL HANTZ, BROKE
DOWN.
YOU FEEL A RESPONSIBILITY TO
RECLAIM THE FAMILY NAME IN A
POSITIVE LIGHT?
I'M GONNA DO IT.
Jeff: FOURTH PERSON VOTED
OUT THE "SURVIVOR: SOUTH
PACIFIC."
IN THE END, STACEY WAS VOTED OUT
AND SHE PASSED ON A HUG FROM
COACH ON HER WAY TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
TRACY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
WHERE SHE WILL SOON BATTLE WITH
HER OLD FRIEND, CHRIS CHRISTINE.
14 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT?
HELLO?
CHRISTINE, IT'S STACEY.
HEY!
OH, BE CAREFUL.
OKAY.
YOU GOT IT SO COMFY OVER HERE.
I WAS HOPING IT WOULDN'T BE
YOU.
I KNOW.
BUT THAT'S OKAY.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M GOOD, I'M GOOD.
THEM SNAKES OVER THERE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
GIRL.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
CHRISTINE, GUESS WHO IS
RUNNING THINGS?
COACH.
I-- I KNEW IT.
EVERYBODY-- THEY WERE AT
TRIBAL ACTING LIKE EVERYTHING IS
HUNKY-DORY.
IT AIN'T HUNKY-DORY.
YOU WHO TALK TO.
I TALK TO ALL THE GIRLS, I'M
DOING THIS.
YEAH--
LIES STRAIGHT FROM HELL.
ALL Y'ALL GONNA GO TO HELL WITH
GASOLINE DROPPED ON YOU.
JUST SURVIVE.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
TRIBAL WAS SO FAKE,
SUFFICIENCY SO FAKE.
THAT IS NOT ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY
ON THE BLUE TRIBE.
COACH COMHERE, AND HE TRY TO ACT
LIKE HE'S JUST ALL HOLIER THAN
THOU.
HE IS NOTHING BUT A JOKE.
WHEN THEY FIND OUT THE REALLY
TRUTH ABOUT HIM... I'M GOING TO
START UP A BEE'S NEST AND LET
THE RED TRIBE KNOW COACH IS IN
CONTROL OVER THERE.
I'M ANYTHING TO SPILL EVERYTHING
I KNOW IS GOING ON OVER THERE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
HOW ARE YOU BRANDON?
I'M DOING GOOD.
GOOD MORNING, EVERYONE.
I'M SORRY TO WAKE EVERYBODY BUT
WE HAVE TREE MAIL.
TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS EMOTIONAL,
MAN.
THE WAY THAT MIKAYLA ANSWERED
JEFF'S QUESTION WHEN HE ASKED
WHAT SHE DOESN'T LIKE ABOUT ME
THE MOST, SHE SAID, "I DON'T
LIKE HE'S A HANTZ" IT WAS PRETTY
PREJUDICED.
THE WAY SHE HANDLED THAT SHOWS
SHE HAD VERY LITTLE CLASS AT
THAT TIME.
YOU KNOW, THESE ARE REAL PEOPLE
OUT HERE.
THEY HAVE REAL-- THEY HAVE
FEELINGS, YOU KNOW.
AND I DON'T CARE WHAT PEOPLE
THINK ABOUT ME.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I MEAN, I'M A GOOD PERSON.
I'M A GOOD GUY.
AND, YOU KNOW, IF I CAN'T WIN
THE GAME LIKE THAT, THEN I DON'T
NEED TO WIN IT.
OUTWIT, OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
TWO MORE FROM REDEMPTION AND TWO
MORE FROM YOUR TRIBE WIN THE
ATTENTION.
TODAY, CHRISTINE AND STACEY
ARE BATTLING IT OUT AND THE
OTHER TRIBE COULD GET
INTELE FROM US AND AND I'M
HOPING WHEN ALBERT COMES BACK
THAT STACEY AND CHRISTINE KEPT
THEIR MOUTH SHUT.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
CHRISTINE WILL BATTLE AGAINST
STACEY VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
STACEY, WHAT'S IT LIKE FOR YOU
TO SEE YOUR FORMER TRIBE MATES
WHO VOTED YOU OUT?
THOSE-- THOSE ARE LIARS, SO,
RED TEAM, LOOK OUT FOR THOSE
RIGHT THERE, OKAY?
IT WASN'T A TEAM.
IT IS BENJAMIN, ALBERT, AND
SOPHIE.
BUT WHO ARE THEY ANSWERING TO,
BENJAMIN AND ALBERT.
Jeff: BENJAMIN, COACH.
BENJAMIN IS RUNNING THE TEAM.
BENJAMIN MAKES THE DECISIONS.
MAKES ALL THE DECISIONS.
Jeff: WHEN I SAID COACH,
YOU SAID, NO, BENJAMIN.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE?
ADULTS CALL HIM BENJAMIN.
WHETHER HE LIKES IT OR NOT,
IT'S BENJAMIN.
Jeff: SO YOUR WAY OF
FIGHTING BACK IS TO SAY I WILL
NOT HONOR THE COACH NAME.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
WHAT WAS HIS BIRTH NAME?
IT WASN'T COACH.
IT WAS BENJAMIN, WASN'T IT.
AND THE CHILDREN, 26, 22, THEY
LISTEN TO ALL THE BENJAMIN'S
HALLOWEEN JOKES, CHUCK E. CHEESE
JOKES.
THEY WANT IT.
COME ON, EVERY DAY HE GOT A
STORY.
I WASN'T BUYING IT.
NO.
SO, LIKE YESTERDAY, LIKE THE
TRIBAL WAS ALL CAHOOTS, LET'S
GIVE A HUG.
KEEP THAT HUG.
FOR ME.
BECAUSE IT WASN'T REAL.
SOUR GRAPES.
Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S DUEL.
YEAH.
Jeff: TODAY'S DUEL WILL
REQUIRE CONCENTRATION AND
COORDINATION.
YOU'RE GOING TO DROP A BALL DOWN
A CHUTE.
IT WILL SPIRAL DOWNWARD UNTIL IT
FALLS OUT THE BOTTOM WHERE YOU
MUST CATCH IT, PUT IT BACK IN
THE CHUTE.
EVERY FEW MINUTES WE'LL ADD
ANOTHER BALL.
THE BALLS WILL ALTERNATE LEFT
AND RIGHT, MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT TO TRACK THEM.
IF AT ANY POINT A BALL HITS THE
GROUND, YOU'RE OUT OF THE DUEL.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING STAYS
ALIVE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THE LOSER IS OUT OF THIS GAME
FOR GOOD.
THIS IS IT, ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
YOU GO, GIRL.
YOU, TOO.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO.
TAKE YOUR FIRST BALL.
AND DROP IT IN THE CHUTE.
WE ARE ON.
YOU WANT TO LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER
DAY IN THIS GAME?
YOU MUST WIN.
CONCENTRATION.
THAT IS THE KEY TO THIS
CHALLENGE.
ONE BALL IS PRETTY EASY.
ALL RIGHT, YOU HAVE 10 SECONDS
TO ADD ANOTHER BALL.
REMEMBER TO THINK ABOUT YOUR
SPACING.
IT'S CRITICAL IN THIS CHALLENGE.
TWO BALLS A LITTLE TRICKIER.
AND THEY'RE ALTERNATING LEFT AND
RIGHT.
HARD TO TRACK.
YOU GUYS ARE DOING GREAT.
KEEP CONCENTRATING.
ALL RIGHT, YOU HAVE 10 SECONDS.
THINK ABOUT YOUR SPACING.
STACEY DROPS A BALL RIGHT OFF
THE BAT, NOT PAYING ANY
ATTENTION TO WHAT THE OTHER
BALLS ARE DOING.
YOU HAVE 10 SECONDS AND SHE
JUST THROWS IT IN.
SO STUPID.
Jeff: CHRISTINE TAKING HER
TIME, PLACING IT.
USING THE SPACING.
EVERYBODY'S GOOD.
THREE BALLS NOW.
VERY DIFFICULT.
ABSOLUTE CONCENTRATION IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
CHRISTINE WITH A NICE SAVE.
THERE ARE NO TOMORROWS FOR THE
LOSER.
YOU WILL BE OUT OF THIS GAME FOR
GOOD.
CHRISTINE WITH ANOTHER NICE
SAVE.
JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
Jeff: YOU GUYS HAVE A GOOD
RHYTHM GOING.
YOU'RE DOING A GREAT JOB.
STACEY DROPS A BALL.
CHRISTINE STAYS ALIVE ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND!
( APPLAUSE )
GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: STACEY.
YEAH.
Jeff: WHAT DID THIS
ADVENTURE MEAN FOR YOU?
I CHALLENGED MYSELF.
THIS IS SOMETHING I NEVER WOULD
HAVE DONE.
YOU KNOW, I'M A FUNERAL
DIRECTOR, MORTICIAN IS WHAT I
AM.
I MEAN, I'M A DIVA.
WHO LIVES LIKE THIS?
BUT IN SPITE OF EVERYTHING I HAD
FUN AND I'M PROUD OF MYSELF.
Jeff: STACEY, YOUR
ADVENTURE HAS COME TO AN END.
OKAY.
Jeff: IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO
GO.
GOOD JOB, STACEY.
DON'T EVEN SAY ANYTHING.
BYE, GIRLS.
Y'ALL STAY STRONG, OKAY.
STRONG WOMAN.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: BYE, STACEY.
Jeff: CHRISTINE, ONCE AGAIN
YOU SEIZED THE MOMENT.
YOU STAYED ALIVE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP AND AWAIT YOUR
NEXT DUEL.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: CONGRATS.
GOOD JOB, GIRL.
GOOD JOB.
THANKS, HOPE TO SEE YOU SOON.
HANG IN THERE.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
WHAT YOU SHARE WITH THE REST OF
YOUR TRIBE MATES, UP TO YOU.
BENJAMIN'S BEEN DOING
EVERYTHING AND ALBERT IS HIS
RIGHT-HAND MAN.
THOSE WERE THINGS I THOUGHT WE
WOULD BE ABLE TO KEEP UNDER THE
RADAR PRETTY WELL.
IT JUST PISSES ME OFF BECAUSE IT
MAKES US LOOK BAD IN FRONT OF
THE OTHER TRIBE AND I KNOW COACH
IS GOING TO BE PISSED.
HEY, GUYS.
HOWDIE.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
HOW WAS IT?
BAD?
IT WAS BAD, DUDE.
STACEY, SHE SAID WE'RE ALL
LIARS.
SHE SAID THAT YOU, SOPHIE,
MYSELF WERE CONTROLLING STUFF.
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
STACEY JUST WENT ON A
RAMPAGE.
REALLY.
BENJAMIN IS RUNNING THE
TRIBE.
BENJAMIN.
WHO'S BENJAMIN?
YOU'RE NOT COACH, YOU'RE
BENJAMIN.
JEFF IS LIKE YOU REFUSE TO
DIGNIFY HIM AS COACH.
HE'S BENJAMIN.
IF ANYBODY CALLS ME BENJAMIN
TO MY FACE I'LL GO NUTS.
MY PARENTS CALL ME COACH.
I'VE BEEN CALLED COACH SINCE I
WAS 18.
STACEY JUST WENT ON A RANT.
STACEY SAID COACH IS RUNNING THE
SHOW, SO NOW AT THE MERGE I'M
PROBABLY GOING TO BE HIT NUMBER
ONE.
IT JUST RUINS MY DAY.
IT SUCTION.
COULD THIS DAY GET REQUEST
WORSE?
FEELING GOOD?
COOL.
YEW LIKE MY LITTLE OMEN.
I LIKE THAT.
THE ALLIANCE BETWEEN ME,
OZZY, KEITH, JIM, AND WHITNEY IS
STILL PRETTY STRONG.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN HAD TO TALK
ABOUT THE VOTE AND WHAT IT WILL
COME DOWN TO AT THE NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, WHICH IS GREAT IF
YOU'RE ONE OF US.
THEN THERE'S OZZY AND MYSELF,
AND I'M KIND OF JUST FOLLOWING
HIS LEAD.
I BELIEVE HE CAN TAKE ME FAR IN
THE GAME AND I THINK WE SEE THE
GAME THE SAME WAY.
WE FEEL THE SAME WAY ABOUT THE
ALLIANCE, ABOUT THE MERGE, ABOUT
MAKING IT FAR.
WE'RE PALS.
TRIP, CHO-CHO MAN.
GOOD STUFF.
I'M THE LITTLE ENGINE THAT
COULD, MAN.
THE LITTLE COCHRAN THAT
COULD.
YEAH, THE LITTLE COCHRAN THAT
THE LITTLE COCHRAN THAT
COULD.
HODO YOU SPELL THAT, C-O-C-H.
YOU WON'T HAVE TO SPELL THAT
ANY TIME SOON.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE SPELLING,
MAN.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE PHONETICS
OR ANYTHING.
KEEP MY NAME AS FAR OFF YOUR
FINGERS AND YOUR TONGUE AS
POSSIBLE.
THEY ARE.
I WORK MY ASS OFF AROUND
CAMP, EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT A BIG
PROVIDER LIKE OZZY OR ANYBODY.
I'M WORKING HARD, AND THEN TO
SEE AS YOUY AND ELYSE SLEEPING
IN EVERY SINGLE DAY, THEY'RE
WRAPPED UP IN THEIR LOVE BLANKET
WELL INTO THE EARLY-- OR LATE
MORNING.
I FIND EVERY LITTLE THING ABOUT
THEM IRRITATING NOW.
YOU'RE A GOOD GUY.
WE'RE BACK!
WE'RE HOME!
READY?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WHO WAS VOTED OUT?
MY GUESS, PUPPET DRESS.
THEY VOTED STATE STACY OUT
PURPLE DRESS!
YES.
I REALLY THOUGHT THEY WOULD
GO FOR WEAK BUT THEY'RE GOING
FOR TEAM COACH.
ANYBODY WHO WASN'T WITH COACH IS
GOING OUT.
COACH IS RUNNING THE SHOWY.
ACTUALLY, THEY CALLED HIM
BENJAMIN.
SHE'S LIKE, WATCH OUT.
BENJAMIN IS IN CHARGE, ALBERT,
SOPHIE.
IT'S NOT UNIFIED.
IT'S NOT--
YEAH.
BASICALLY THEY'RE ALL LIKE HIS
PUPPETS.
COACH, ALBERT.
IF COACH IS STOCK MARKET
HE'LL GET RID OF ALBERT SOON.
I THINK ALBERT AND HE ARE
ALIGNED.
WHY WOULD HE GET RIDE OF
ALBERT?
IF THEY GET RID OF ALBERT--
BEFORE THE HERM.
OZZY MADE ONE BIG MISTAKE.
HE REVEALED IF HE WERE COACH HE
WOULD GET RID OF ALBERT.
THAT'S HUGE INFORMATION BECAUSE
IF OZZY IS SAYING COACH SHOULD
GET ONE OF THE STRONGER PEOPLE
ON HIS TRIBE, THAT'S SAYING OZZY
SHOULD GET RID OF ONE OF THE
STRONGER PEOPLE ON HIS SIDE.
THE TWO STRONG PEOPLE ARE ME AND
KEITH.
STAY HUMBLE, POSITIVE,
UNIFIED.
ONCE I HEARD THAT, I KNEW
WHAT I HAD.
NOTHING SELLS LIKE FEAR.
I'M GOING TO PUT THAT FEAR IN
KEITH TELL HIM TO GET ELYSE GONE
NEXT.
THE DUEL WAS DEFINITELY
PAINFUL TO HEAR SOME OF THE
THINGS THAT WERE SAID-- NOT
PAINFUL PERSONALLY BUT PAINFUL
TOWARDS MY CAUSE.
DESPITE HOW STASE SENOT THE
SHARPEST TOOL IN THE SHED SHE
STILL SAID COACH AND ARE RUNNING
THINGS AND I'M GOING TO HAVE A
TARGET ON MY BACK ONCE WE GO TO
THE MERGE.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY IT GET ME
OUT BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING TO SEE
ME AS A THREAT.
THAT CLUE IS STILL OUT THERE AND
THAT IDOL IS STILL OUT THERE.
I NEED TO FIND IT NOW.
THE CLUE!
GOOD STUFF RIGHT HERE.
"IT'S DEFINITELY NEAR THE
JUNGLE, SOMEWHERE BY THE BEACH.
THE IMPORTANT THING TO REALIZE
IS IT'S JUST BARELY OUT OF
REACH.
YOU COULD STAY DRY IF THE TIDE
IS RIGHT, BUT YOU'LL NEED TO
CLIMB TO HAVE IDOL IN SIGHT."
GOOD THINGS ARE HAPPENING.
THE CLUE KIND OF TOLD ME THE
LOCATION OF THE IDOL IS
SOMEWHERE ON THE BEACH, WHERE
THE TIDE COMES IN KIND OF HIGH,
AND IT'S SOMEWHERE UP OUT OF
REACH IN THE TREE.
ONE BY ONE, I'M GOING TREE AFTER
TREE AFTER TREE.
THE MORE I'M LOOKING, I'M
STARTING TO GET A LITTLE
FLUSTERED.
SO I FIGURED I CAN KILL TWO
BIRDS WITH ONE STONE.
I CAN KIND OF FURNISH GARNER
COACH AND SOPHIE'S TRUST BY
LETEG THEM IN ON THIS IDOL AND I
CAN ALSO HAVE THEM BE HELPERS
FOR ME TO FIND THE IDOL BECAUSE
FRANKLY I THINK I CAN'T DO THIS
BY MYSELF.
I FOUND A CLUE TO THE SECOND
IDOL, AND I KNOW THAT IT'S IN A
TREE.
IT'S HIGH.
AND IT'S BY THE BEACH.
I'M ONLY GOING TO TELL YOU TWO
BECAUSE I TRUST YOU TWO THE
MOST.
THIS IS A HUGE GAME CHANGER.
YEAH, IT IS HUGE.
ALBERT COULDN'T FIND THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL BUT HE'S FOUND A
CLUE.
HE DIDN'T WANT TO TELL THE WHOLE
ALLIANCE SO ONLY THE THREE OF US
KNOW ABOUT THE CLUE, ALBERT,
SOPHIE AND I.
IT WILL BE OUR LITTLE SECRET.
I CHECKED THIS TREE AND THIS
TREE.
I CHECKED TWO TREES OVER THERE
BUT I CAN'T FIND THE IDOL.
IT DEFINITELY SAID IN A TREE?
IT SAYS OUT OF REACH.
YOU WANT TO DO A JOB RIGHT,
YOU DO IT YOURSELF.
SO I JUST SAID TO MYSELF I'VE
GOT TO TAKE THIS INTO MY OWN
HANDS.
OW!
MAYBE I'M GOING ABOUT THIS THE
WRONG WAY.
I DON'T TROOPS IN IT'S YOUR WILL
THAT I FIND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND I BEG YOU TO LET ME
FIND IT TODAY.
COME ON, BABY.
COME TO ME.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE IT.
ASK AND YOU SHALL RECEIVE.
COACH WADE HAS FOUND THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, AND LO AND
BEHOLD, LOOK WHAT WE HAVE HERE.
A GOLDEN LITTLE GEM FOR COACH
WADE TO HOLD ON TO.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY, ARE THE STARS
ALINING FOR COACH OR WHAT?
THIS IS THE MOST EXCITING MOMENT
IN 67 DAYS FOR COACH PLAYING
THIS GAME.
MOMENT OF TRUTH.
WE'VE GOT THIS GAME BY THE
BALLS, GUY.
THIS MORNING I THOUGHT TO
MYSELF, COULD THIS DAY GET ANY
WORSE?
BUT NOW COACH IS A HAPPY MAN.
THINGS COULDN'T BE GOING BETTER.
I HAVE TO GET AHOLD OF MYSELF
AND SAY DRAGON, JUST GET BACK IN
THERE.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY I'M PLAYING
THE GAME WITH YOU TWO.
CAN'T GO TOO CRAZY.
I'M NOT RUNNING THE SHOW, BUT AT
THE MOMENT, PRETTY CLOSE.
♪ ♪ ♪
ARE YOU READY TO DO THIS?
LET'S DO IT, MAN.
THE OCEAN IS MY CANVAS, AND THE
FISH ARE MY PALETTE.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE ANY
OUTDOORSY SKILLS, BUT I FIGURE,
YOU KNOW, I GOTTA STEP UP.
I'M SLIGHTLY NERVOUS GOING ON
THE BOAT FOR THE FIRST TIME
BECAUSE I BRING ZERO EXPERIENCE,
ZERO ABILITY, AND ZERO
CONFIDENCE.
SO WE SIT ON THE LEFT?
ON THE RIGHT.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
PROVE ANYTHING TOWARDS BEING
ABLE TO CATCH FISH.
THAT'S LEFT TO OZZY.
BUT I HOPE THIS WILL BE A
BONDING EXPERIENCE SO THAT I'M
NOT VIEWED AS ONE OF THE GIRLS
WHO HANGS AROUND CAMP WHILE THE
TRUE MEN GO OUT FISHING.
I THINK MY REPUTATION IN
"SURVIVOR" IS I'VE BEEN THE GUY
THAT HAS BEEN ABLE TO GO OUT AND
HUNT FISH AND PROVIDE PEOPLE
WITH SUSTENANCE, BUT FISHING'S
NOT EASY.
IT MIGHT LOOK EASY TO SOMEBODY
WATCHING AT HOME, PUT IT REALLY
IS VERY DIFFICULT, AND IT TAKES
A LOT OUT OF ME.
I GET CUT UP ALL THE TIME.
JUST THE FACT THAT I'VE GOT TO
HOLD MY BREATH CONTINUOUSLY AND
SORT OF STAY IN ONE POSITION.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE UNDERWATER
YOGA.
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT.
NICE!
I'M TOTALLY HAPPY TO PLAY THE
PROVIDER ROLE, AND I THINK IT'S
GOING TO PUT ME IN A STRONGER
POSITION THAN ANYONE ELSE.
IT'S LIKE I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
REALLY BECOMING MY TRIBE.
OH, YA!
HOLY CRAP!
AWESOME, WOW.
YEAH, WE GOT 11.
HOLY CRAP.
HAVING WATCHED "COOK ISLANDS"
AND "FANS VERSUS FAVORITES" YOU
SEE OZZY AS KIND OF SUPERHUMAN
GUY THAT CAN DO NO WRONG, BUT
OZZY, IT'S THIS MIDDLE AGED OZZY
WHO HAS A FEW MOMENTS OF GLORY
EACH DAY WHERE HE RUNS OUT AND
GETS US SOME FISH BUT OTHERWISE,
HE'S KIND OF A LAZY ASS.
HE'S PACKAGING THE ARROGANT
FISHER BOY, JUNGLE BOY, WHO
FEELS LIKE HE CAN DO NO WRONG
AND THAT HE'S ENTITLED TO OUR
DEFERENCE.
THE MORE HE ACTS LIKE THIS, IT'S
GOING TO COME BACK TO BITE HIM
IN THE ASS.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
RICK, BIG REACTION SEEING THAT
PIG.
THAT'S NICE!
( LAUGHTER )
Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
DAWN, I MUST TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, EACH
TRIBE WILL HAVE A ROASTED PIG ON
A SPIT.
WITH YOUR HANDS TIED BEHIND YOUR
BACK, YOU WILL RACE TO CHEW OFF
AS MUCH MEAT AS YOU CAN.
YOU MAY BE TEMPTED TO EAT IT.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO WIN, PUT IT
IN THE BASKET.
THE TRIBE THAT SPITS THE MOST
MEAT IN THEIR BASKET AT THE END
OF 10 MINUTES WINS IMMUNITY.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNING TRIBE
EARNS REWARD
( APPLAUSE )
IS THAT BREAD?
Jeff: VEGGIES, SPICES, BIG
LOAF OF BREAD.
WE WANT SOME CARBS, MAN.
WE GOTTA HAVE SOME.
Jeff: IN ADDITION, THE
WINNING TRIBE WILL HAVE ANOTHER
HIDDEN CLUE WAITING FOR THEM
BACK AT CAMP.
FIND THE CLUE, THAT WILL HELP
YOU FIND THE HIDDEN IDOL.
WORTH PLAYING FOR.
YEAH.
OH, YEAH!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ANY WAY YOU CAN GET THAT MEAT
OFF USING YOUR MOUTH, AND THEN
WRING IT BACK AND SPIT IT IN THE
BASKET.
IT WILL BE LITTLE PIECES IN THE
BEGINNING, AND THEN PROBABLY
BIGGER PIECES TOWARD THE END AS
YOU START WORKING.
COME ON, GUYS!
BIG ONE, BIG ONE!
DOUBLE TIME, GUYS, COME ON!
Jeff: COCHRAN GETTING IN
THERE.
ELYSE GETTING IN THERE.
COACH'S FACE COVERED IN SAUCE.
EVERYBODY WORKING HARD IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
DAWN WITH A BIG HUNK OF MEAT.
THE ENTIRE UPOLU TRIBE COMING
BACK WITH A MOUTH FULL.
COACH GNAWING OFF SOMETHING BIG.
THAT MEAT IS STUCK IN KEITH'S
TEETH.
HE CAN'T GET IT OUT.
DAWN GOING TO PULL IT OUT.
THAT IS TEAM WORK RIGHT THERE!
BRANDON BACK FOR MORE.
OZZY TRYING TO GET IN THERE AND
GET DEEP, TRYING TO GET
SOMETHING BIG GOING.
SO GOOD!
GOOD JOB, GUYS!
Jeff: RICK WITH A HUGE
PIECE OF MEAT.
COME OALL THE WAY!
ALL THE WAY, GUYS, ALL THE WAY!
Jeff: ELYSE, WOW!
ALBERT ALMOST KNOCKS OVER HIS
ENTIRE TRIBE'S BASKET.
THAT WAS DISGUSTING, JIM EDNA
HAS MEAT STUCK IN HER MOUTH.
COACH HAS TO RIP IT OUT.
SOMEBODY RIP THIS.
Jeff: NOW BRANDON CAN'T GET
HIS OUT.
RICK PULLS IT OUT.
THANK YOU, RICK.
Jeff: BOTH TRIBES GETTING
TO KNOW EACH OTHER IN A WHOLE
NEW WAY.
THIS IS A DISGUSTING CHALLENGE.
OUT OF MY MOUTH, OUT OF MY
MOUTH.
Jeff: BRANDON NEEDS TO
FLOSS.
30 SECONDS LEFT!
BOTH TRIBES GETTING A LOT OF
MEAT OFF OF THIS PIG.
RICK DROPS ONE ON THE GROUND.
IS HE GOING TO LEAVE IT?
HE'S LEAVING IT!
MIKAYLA WILL PICK IT UP.
SHE'S NOT TOO PROUD.
WE ARE VERY CLOSE.
COME OEVERYBODY GET A BITE
AND GO.
GET A BITE AND GO.
Jeff: 15 SECONDS.
SAVAII NEEDS SOMETHING BIG RIGHT
NOW.
JIM WITH A HUGE PIECE OF MEAT AT
THE END!
THAT WILL MAKEY A DIFFERENCE IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
FIVE SECONDS LEFT, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE, WE'RE DONE!
PULL AWAY!
LET GO, OZZY.
LET GO.
WHATEVER IS IN YOUR MOUTH, PUT
IN YOUR BASKET, THEN WALK AWAY.
SOMEBODY HAS TO GET THIS OUT
OF MY TEETH.
Jeff: OZZY GIVES COCHRAN A
NICE LITTLE KISS TO GET THAT
LAST LITTLE BIT AND THIS MIGHT
BE VERY CLOSE.
DRUM ROLL ON SOPHIE'S BACK.
Jeff: START WITH SAVAII.
PAST THE 10 POUNDS.
THAT'S A LOT OF MEAT, FOLKS.
THAT IS A LOT OF MEAT.
Jeff: PAST THE 20 POUNDS.
WE'RE AT 22 POUNDS, 12 OUNCES
FOR SAVAII.
( APPLAUSE )
THERE'S 10 POUNDS.
THERE'S 20 POUNDS.
NO WAY.
22 POUND, 12 OUNCES IS THE
MARK TO BEAT.
22 POUNDS, 14 OUNCES.
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD
BY TWO OUNCES.
WHOOO!
NO, WAY.
Jeff: UPOLU,
CONGRATULATIONS.
HARD FOUGHT CHALLENGE.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
IN ADDITION, NICE REWARD TO TAKE
WITH YOU BACK TO CAMP.
AND ANOTHER CLUE TO THE LOCATION
OF A HIDDEN IDOL WILL BE WAITING
FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
IT IS HIDDEN AS WELL.
IN ADDITION, BECAUSE YOU WON,
YOU CAN TAKE HOME ALL THE MEAT
YOU COLLECTED.
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT, BABY!
Jeff: COME GET YOUR REWARD.
WE'LL FRY THE MEAT UP AND GET
ALL THE SPIT OFF IT AND WE'LL BE
GOOD.
WASH ALL THE SPIT OFF AND COW
DOWN!
THAT'S SO AWESOME.
THIS AIN'T NO JOKE.
THAT WAS CRAZY CLOSE.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SAVAII,
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL
TONIGHT.
HE'S ALL BUSINESS.
LOOK AT HIM.
WATCHING MY DAD AND MY MOM
COOK AND MY GRABBED MA, A BUNCH
OF CAJUNS, MAN.
THEY JUST COOK, COOK, COOK.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, THE FOOD IS
READY.
THERE ARE A LOT OFS OF UPS AND
DOWNS JUST IN GENERAL IN THE
GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
TODAY WAS POSITIVE ENERGY, MAN.
I BELIEVE WE'RE A TEAM AND A
FAMILY.
OH, MY GOSH!
THIS IS SO GOOD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK BUDDY?
THE TASTE OF VICTORY, MAN!
I'M GOING CRAZY RIGHT NOW I'M SO
EXCITED.
THE BEST THING ABOUT TODAY'S
CHALLENGE-- BEEP-BEEP-- WE'RE
BACK IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT, BABY.
WE OWN IT NOW.
I MEAN, THIS IS FREAKING
UNBELIEVABLE, MAN.
IN ALL HONESTY THE WHOLE BACK
SIDE OF ONE OF MY MOLARS IS
GONE.
IT JUST CAME DOWN TO TEAM
MOUTH AND VOLUME SIZE.
MY LIPS HURT SO BAD.
YEAH, WE'RE ALL GOING TO HAVE
PIG GUT BREAKOUT TOMORROW ON OUR
SKIN.
WE'RE PROBABLY ALSO GOG HAVE
ORAL HERPES.
WHAT? !
WHAT?
I'M SURE SOMEBODY DOES.
DOESN'T EVERYBODY HAVE HERPES?
WHAT!
DON'T 99% OF HUMAN BEINGS
HAVE HERPES.
OKAY, HARVARD.
I DON'T THINK SO.
GETTING A COLD SORE, THAT'S
HERPES.
I HAVE NEVER HAD A COLD SORE.
YOU'RE NOT LIVING, THEN.
YOU'RE TELLING USS YOU JUST
GAVE US COLD SORES?
NO I'M SAYING I'M GOING TO
GET IT FROM ONE OF YOU.
ANYBODY WANT ME TO OPEN A
COCONUT?
I'M GETTING GOOD AT IT.
HE'S TRYING SO HARD.
I KNOW.
ANYBODY WANTS THIS COCONUT?
NO.
IS THERE JUICE IN IT?
TONS IN IT.
I'LL TAKE A LITTLE SIP.
OZZY, YOU WANT ANY?
AS SOON AS WE GOT BACK FROM
THE CHALLENGE, COCHRAN
DEFINITELY MADE A POINT OF
PUTTING ON A DISPLAY OF WORKING.
I'M TRYING TO PROVE MY WORTH
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
HE WORKED HARDER THAN I'VE
SEEN HIM WORK THE WHOLE TIME OUT
HERE.
IT JUST SUCKS IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU KNOW.
I THINK PRETTY MUCH EVERYBODY ON
THE TRIBE FEELS HE IS THE
WEAKEST LINK, AND I THINK
EVERYBODY FEELS GOOD ABOUT
LETTING HIM GO TONIGHT.
SO THAT'S THE PLAN, RIGHT?
IT'S COCHRAN.
OKAY.
OZZY'S PRETTY CLEAR THAT HE
WANTS COCHRAN GONE, BUT IN MY
OPINION, IT'S TIME TO BREAK UP
THAT ALLIANCE WITH OZZY AND
ELYSE.
RIGHT NOW, I THINK YOU, ME,
AND JIM ARE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE
IN TERMS OF WANTING TO GET RID
OF ELYSE NEXT.
RIGHT, ELYSE HAS TO GO.
SHE'S FINE WITH ELYSE FIRST.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW WHO THE
LINCHPIN IS GOING TO BE IS
KEITH.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OKAY.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE COCHRAN AND
DAWN BUT IN A TRIBE OF SEVEN,
YOU NEED FOUR.
I GOTTA FIND THAT FOURTH VOTE TO
GET ELYSE OUT.
I GOTTA TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING THAT CAME UP THAT I
DIDN'T LIKE.
SOMETHING KIND OF BIG, ACTUALLY.
IT RAISED MY EYEBROWS A LOT.
THE ONLY THING GOOD THAT CAME
OUT OF THE REDEMPTION ISLAND
INFORMATION IS I GOT A PIECE OF
FEAR THEY CAN PLANT IN KEITH TO
HELP HIM VOTE WITH ME AGAINST
ELYSE TONIGHT.
OZZY IS TALKING ABOUT COACH
NEEDS TO GET OUT ALBERT
BEFOREHAND.
AND I'M LIKE-- SO, IMMEDIATELY,
IF HE'S THINKING THAT COACH
NEEDS TO GET OUT ALBERT, THAT
MEANS HE'S THINKING HE NEEDS TO
GET OUT ONE OF US PREMERGE.
AND I DON'T-- HERE'S THE THING,
HE CAN'T DO IT-- LIKE COCHRAN IS
DRIVING ME FREAKING CRAZY.
I KNOW,.
BUT IF WE GET RID OF ELYSE
FIRST, HE CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
I KNOW.
I AGREE.
WE NEED ELYSE FIRST GONE.
KEITH AND I GET ON THE SAME
PAGE WITHIN ABOUT 30 SECONDS.
SO IT'S LOOKING PRETTY STRONGLY
LIKE ELYSE IS NEXT.
THEN WHAT HAPPENS?
I DON'T THINK WE TELL OZZY.
BUT THEN HE'S NOT GOING TO
TRUST US.
TONIGHT'S VOTE IS SUPPOSED TO GO
JIM, DAWN, COCHRAN, AND THEY
VOTE ELYSE, AND THEN ELYSE AND
OZZY ARE GOING TO VOTE FOR
COCHRAN.
SO THAT LEAVES ME AND WHITNEY
FOR A LITTLE ROOM TO PLAY.
WE GOTTA DO THAT.
BECAUSE THEN WE CAN KIND OF DO
WHATEVER WE WANT.
THE FIRST ALLIANCE I MADE WAS
ME AND OZZY, SO TONIGHT'S VOTE
IS GOING TO BE REALLY SCARY
BECAUSE ELYSE GETS BLINDSIDED,
IN A SENSE, OZZY GETS
BLINDSIDED.
SO HOW IS OZZY GOING TO TRUST ME
WHEN HE THINKS WE'RE ALL VOTING
FOR COCHRAN?
THAT'S THE QUESTION THAT I'M
GOING TO HAVE TO TRY TO FIGURE
OUT.
AND YOU'RE, LIKE, 100%
THINKING WE SHOULD GO WITH ELYSE
NOW?
YES, NO, I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH, I JUST WANT TO MAKE
SURE THAT WE'VE THOUGHT
EVERYTHING THROUGH.
ELYSE AND OZZY ARE LIKE THIS.
AND I DON'T THINK OZZY'S GOING
TO LIKE IT IF WE ALL VOTE HER
OFF, AND THERE GOES OUR
ALLIANCE.
SO OZZY WANTS COCHRAN RIGHT
NOW.
WHAT ONE SO BAD IF WE VOTED
COCHRAN OUT?
I DON'T KNOW.
SO IS IT BETTER TO GET ELYSE
OUT NOW OR LATER?
I DON'T KNOW.
KEITH I ARE STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO WEASEL OUR WAY
AROUND THIS AND STILL COME OUT
IN OUR ALLIANCE WITH OZZY.
IT'S HARD.
I WISH WE COULD LET THOSE THREE
VOTE FOR ELYSE AND US TWO VOTE
NOT COCHRAN, JUST SOMEONE ELSE.
WE'RE ALL GOOD.
ELYSE IS NEXT.
REALLY?
YEAH, YEAH.
SERIOUSLY?
100%.
REALLY?
FOR THE FIRST TIME I'M NOT
FEELING THAT BAD ABOUT MY
CHANCES GOING INTO TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL.
WORST-CASE SCENARIO, I GET SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
BUT I REALLY DON'T WANT TO GET
SENT TO REDEMPTION.
I DON'T THINK IF OZZY THINKS WE
ARE ALL AGAINST HIM.
WE ARE ALL AGAINST HIM.
HE WILL BE AGAINST ME WHEN WE
VOTE OUT HIS HAMMOCK SWEETHEART.
WHICH IS WHAT I HOPE WILL HAPPEN
TONIGHT.
Y
Jeff: OZZY, WE'RE 14 DAYS
IN, ROUGHLY A THIRD OF THE WAY
INTO THE ADVENTURE.
HAVING PLAYED TWICE BEFORE,
WHERE ARE WE AT RIGHT NOW FROM A
GAME POINT OF VIEW?
YOU KNOW, A THIRD OF THE WAY
IN, MERGE IS STILL TOO FAR OFF
TO BE THAT WORRIED ABOUT IN
TERMS OF THE TRUST OF THE GROUP.
SO IT'S ALL ABOUT KEEPING US A
STRONG AS POSSIBLE.
Jeff: ELYSE, HOW DO YOU
DEFINE A STRONG TRIBE MEMBER?
I THINK IN THIS GAME A STRONG
TRIBE MEMBER IS SOMEBODY WHO IS
STRONG ACROSS THE BOARD.
SO SOMEBODY WHO CAN DELIVER WHAT
THEY'RE EXPECTED IN A CHALLENGE.
SOMEBODY WHO CAN CONTRIBUTE
AROUND CAMP LIFE.
SOMEBODY WHO HAS GOT SOCIAL
SKILLS AND GRACES THAT CAN HELP
UNIFY PEOPLE, KEEPING THE GROUP
TOGETHER.
Jeff: COCHRAN, YOU'VE
GOTTEN VOTES EVERY TIME WE'VE
BEEN AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
RIGHT.
Jeff: WHEN YOU HEAR ELYSE
SAY I WANT SOMEBODY STRONG.
DOES YOUR ANTENNA GO UP
THINKING AM I ONCE AGAIN GOING
TO BE GETTING VOTES BECAUSE MY
LEGS AREN'T TREE TRUNKS?
YEAH, THE NOVELTY OF
ATTENDING TRIBAL COUNCIL HAS
WORN OFF FOR ME.
IN TERMS OF CHALLENGES,
CHALLENGES RUN SUCH A HUGE GAMUT
OF THINGS.
I THINK WE ALL DID A FANTASTIC
JOB AT TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
IT CAME DOWN TO TWO OUNCES.
THAT MADE IT ESPECIALLY
DEVASTATING.
Jeff: TWO OUNCES IS ONE
EXTRA WIGHT.
JIM, WAS THERE ANY GOING BACK
OVER THINKING--
EVERY SUCCESS ONE OF US DID
BECAUSE WE ALL SAY WE GAVE 100%
BUT THEN IT'S LIKE
WOULDA-COULD-A-SHOULD-A.
THIS WAS ONE WHERE IRONICALLY
ENOUGH WE ALL HAD MORE INJURIES
DURING THIS CHALLENGE THAN ANY
OF OUR OTHER CHALLENGES
COMBINED.
Jeff: GIVE ME THE RUNDOWN.
WHO HAS AN INJURY.
FROM TODAY'S CHALLENGE?
FROM TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
Jeff: JIM, WHAT'S YOUR
INJURY.
I HAVE A BUN OF CUTS IN MY
MOUTH.
Jeff: ELYSE.
CUTS.
Jeff: DAWN.
BROKEN TOOTH.
Jeff: WHITNEY?
JUST LIPS.
Jeff: COCHRAN.
I HAVEN'T BEEN WEARING MY
RETAINER AS A SHOULD HAVE BEEN.
I DEFINITELY FELT MY TEETH
SHIFTING.
Jeff: COCHRAN, ARE YOU
BEING SILLY OR ARE YOU 100%
SINCERE.
I'M WARPING THE ARRANGEMENT
OF MY TEETH.
Jeff: SMILE, LET ME SEE.
THAT'S NOT A SMILE.
IT'S A GRIMACE, BUT...
Jeff: DAWN, COCHRAN'S NEED
TO ASSESS AND REASSESS, THAT'S
NOT A SMILE, THAT'S A GRIMACE.
HIGHWAY OFTEN IS THAT CHARMING
AND HOW OFTEN IS IT ANNOYING?
I THINK COCHRAN'S ENDEARING.
HE'S A LITTLE BIT OF A CHARACTER
TO ME, BUT I THINK THIS IS ALSO
A GAME ABOUT BRINGING PEOPLE
TOGETHER THAT WOULD NEVER BE
TOGETHER.
SO PART OF ME IS LEARNING TO BE
REALLY TOLERANT.
LIKE TODAY WHEN WE CAME BACK
FROM THE CHALLENGE, HE SAID
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY WE COULD
HAVE SOME COMMUNICABLE DISEASE
BECAUSE WE ALL HAD OUR MOUTHS
AGAINST THE SPIT.
AND I JUST THOUGHT I DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU GET THAT.
IT WAS JUST HILARIOUS BUT NOT.
Jeff: KEITH, EVERYBODY ELSE
WAS KIND OF LAUGHING.
YOU HAD A DIFFERENT REACTION.
YEAH, IT WAS NASTY.
I DON'T WANT A SUPPOSED DISEASE
FROM SOMEONE ELSE'S MOUTH.
YEAH, THE INTENTIONS WERE TO
MAYBE MAKE EVERYONE LAUGH, BUT I
THINK IN THE END, YEAH, IT
GROSSED EVERYONE OUT.
Jeff: COCHRAN, YOU CAN'T
CATCH A BREAK.
IT'S HORRIBLE.
IT'S-- IT'S DEVASTATING.
I KNOW THESE ARE KIND OF
LIGHT-HEARTED COMMENTS, BUT THEY
DO HURT.
I MEAN TRIBAL COUNCIL IS ALWAYS
LIKE NEXT TIME I'M GOING TO BE
BETTER.
I COULD OBSESS ABOUT EVERYTHING
I DO OUT HERE--
AND PROBABLY WILL TONIGHT.
I PROBABLY WILL TONIGHT IF
THERE IS A TONIGHT.
Jeff: ELYSE, CAN YOU FEEL
FOR SOMEBODY LIKE COCHRAN?
OH, I CAN COMPLETELY FEEL FOR
COCHRAN.
I KNOW THAT IT'S HARD TO BE IN A
POSITION WHERE PEOPLE ARE
LOOKING AT YOU AND POINTING OUT
THINGS THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO
HEAR.
I MEAN, WE'VE ALL BEEN IN THAT
POSITION.
WE'VE ALL BEEN PICKED LAST FOR
SOCCER OUT ON THE PLAYGROUND,
YOU KNOW.
Jeff: COCHRAN, ARE YOU
TYPICALLY PICKED LAST FOR
SOCCER?
I DON'T PUT MYSELF IN A
POSITION WHERE I'M PLAYING
SOCCER.
( LAUGHTER ).
BUT ALL THENEROSES AND SELF-DEP
RAICATION ASIDE, I THINK I GET
ALONG WELL WITH PEOPLE.
I MAY HAVE CERTAIN QUIRKS THAT
PEOPLE FIND ACNIG, BUT THAT
ASIDE, I THINK PEOPLE, OR AT
LEAST A GOOD NUMBER OF PEOPLE,
DO TAKE TO ME.
Jeff: ELYSE, GIVEN
EVERYTHING THAT COCHRAN'S GONE
THROUGH, THE LAST TWO TRIBAL
COUNCILS AND AGAIN TONIGHT,
WOULD IT BE HARD TO VOTE HIM
OUT?
ONE THING TO APPRECIATE ABOUT
HIM IS THAT HE SO LOVES AND
KNOWS THE GAME THAT WHETHER HE
STAYS, WHETHER HE GOES TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND, HE'S GOING TO
APPRECIATE THE EXPERIENCE.
Jeff: JIM, IS THERE
ANYTHING ABOUT THE VOTE THAT'S
PERSONAL OR IS IT ABSOLUTELY
STRATEGY?
YOU KNOW, THERE'S ALWAYS A
PERSONAL ELEMENT TO IT.
SO EVEN WHEN I GO BACK THERE AND
WRITE DOWN A NAME THAT'S IN MY
MIND 100% STRATEGIC, IT'S STILL
PERSONAL BECAUSE I KNOW HOW IT'S
GOING TO AFFECT THAT PERSON WHEN
THEY SEE THEIR NAME ON THERE.
Jeff: OKAY, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
JIM, YOU'RE UP.
SORRY, ELYSE, THIS HAS MORE
TO DO WITH KEEPING OZZY WEAK.
THIS IS THE SECOND-TO HISTORY
LAST STOP ON THE TRAIN.
SORRY, MAN.
HOPE YOU GET THAT SECOND CHANCE.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, COCHRAN.
ELYSE.
COCHRAN.
THAT'S TWO VOTES COCHRAN, ONE
VOTE ELYSE.
ELYSE.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES COCHRAN,
TWO VOTES ELYSE.
DAWN.
ONE VOTE DAWN.
DAWN, WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES DAWN, TWO VOTES
COCHRAN, TWO VOTES ELYSE, ONE
VOTE LEFT.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC"
ELYSE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ELYSE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
JUDGING FROM THE LOOK ON ELYSE'S
FACE, I'D SAY THAT WAS YOUR
FIRST BLINDSIDE.
IN THIS GAME JUST TOOK A BIG
TURN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
BRANDON LOOKS LIKE RUSSELL.
I'M HAVING FLASH BACKS IT SCARES
THE HECK FOR ME.
I'LL PLAY FOR MYSELF.
AND YOU GUYS CAN PLAY FOR
YOURSELF.
I'M WHAT I CALL A FREE AGENT.
I HOPE HE CONTINUES TO BE A
CRY BABY BECAUSE IT'S GREAT FOR
ME.
COCHRAN, HELP US.
EVERYTHING, FLIP!
Jeff:A SAVAII CANNOT EVEN
GET THEIR COCONUTS OFF THE
TROUGH!
SO TONIGHT AT TRIBAL, I HAVE
TO ADMIT IT WAS A TOTAL
SURPRISE.
EVERYBODY LIKES TO THINK THAT
THEY'RE FRIENDS WITH EVERYBODY,
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
THAT'S JUST NOT THE CASE SO THE
TRUST IS FOREVER BROKEN BECAUSE
HIGHWAY CAN YOU KNOW WHO TO
TRUST AFTER FEELING SO BETRAYED
AND FEELING SO BETRAYED BY
SEVERAL PEOPLE.