Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": 16 AMERICANS WERE
MAROONED ON A REMOTE SOUTH
PACIFIC ISLAND, EACH WITH A
STORY TO TELL.
I AM, BY FAR, THE MOST
"SURVIVOR" SAVVY PLAYER EVER TO
PLAY THE GAME.
I'VE WON OVER 20 POKER
TOURNAMENTS AND OWN TWO MEDICAL
MARIJUANA DISPENSARIES.
I'M A RETIRED NEW YORK CITY
POLICE DETECTIVE AND I'M OPENLY
GAY.
I'M A LITTLE BIT NERVOUS TO
SEE WHO IT IS.
Jeff: THEY WERE JOINED BY
TWO FORMER SURVIVORS, COACH,
HOWENT TO UPOLO, AND OZZY WHO
BEHIND TO SAVAII.
NOT EVERYONE WAS THRILLED WITH
THE NEW ARRIVALS.
CHRISTINE EVEN CHALLENGED THEM.
THEY'RE TEMPORARY PLAYERS.
Jeff: OZZY WINS FOR SAVAII!
AFTER OZZY DEFEATED COACH IN A
HEAD TO HEAD BATTLE, EDNA BECAME
COACH'S ONLY FRIEND.
BACK AT CAMP, COACH WENT TO
WORK.
HE FORGED A BOND WITH BRANDON,
AND SUDDENLY, HE HAD TWO
FRIENDS.
STILL IN TROUBLE, HE WORKED HIS
WAY INTO A CONVERSATION--
I MET A DRAGON SLAYER!
Jeff: ...AND WALK AWAY WITH
AN ALLIANCE OF FIVE, CONSISTING
OF ALL FOUR MEN ON HIS TRIBE AND
ONE WOMAN, SOPHIE.
I THINK I'M CITY PRETTY RIGHT
NOW.
Jeff: HIS WILD CARD WAS
BRANDON, WHO WAS STRUGGLING WITH
A DANGEROUS SECRET.
I AM RUSSELL HANTZ'S NEPHEW.
I WILL NEVER TELL THEM MY LAST
NAME.
Jeff: AT OZZY'S TRIBE THERE
WAS NO SECRETS.
I TRY TO BE A PROVIDER.
THAT'S MY REAL PURPOSE IN LIFE.
Jeff: MIKAYLA IS A SCORING
MACHINE!
SEMHAR WAY SHORT.
IN ONE OF THE CLOSEST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES ON RECORD-- MIKAYLA,
THAT MIGHT DO IT!
COACH'S TRIBE SQUEAKED OUT A
WIN?
UPOLO WINS IMMUNITY!
SORRY, GUYS.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
IT CAME DOWN TO THE TWO WEAKEST,
SEMHAR AND COCHRAN, BUT COCHRAN
SAVED HIMSELF BY PROMISE TO
IMPROVE.
I'M GOING TO BE YOUR JEANIE
IN A BOTTLE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO RUB, ACTUALLY.
I'LL JUST COME OUT AND DO IT.
Jeff: SEMHAR, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
NOW SEMHAR IS BANISHED TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND, AND THE
PRESSURE SOCOCHRAN TO MAKE GOOD
ON HIS PROMISE BEFORE IT IS TOO
LATE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
DEFINITELY LIKE A BIG PART OF
THIS GAME IS LIKE KEEPING YOUR
MIND IN CHECK AND IT'S REALLY
HARD TO DO THAT WHEN YOU FEEL
ABANDONED BY YOUR TEAM.
I GAVE THEM MY EVERY LEFT
STRENGTH, AND THEY SENT ME TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
FIGURES.
"LIFE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU WILL HAVE SOME BASIC
SUPPLIES TO HELP YOU MAINTAIN
YOUR WORLD HERE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
IF YOU WIN DUEL, YOU'LL REMAIN
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND AND WILL
STILL BE ALIVE IN THE GAME.
IF YOU LOSE YOUR DUEL, YOU WILL
BE OUT OF THE GAME AND MUST
LEAVE REDEMPTION ISLAND."
MAYBE I'M JUST BEING
OVER-EMOTIONAL BUT I JUST HAVE
ABANDONMENT ISSUES.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW PEOPLE
CAN BE SO COLD HEARTED.
BUT ONE OF THE WAYS THAT I'VE
TURNED MY PAIN INTO POSSIVITY IS
THROUGH POETRY.
SOMETIMES I WONDER IF I REALLY
MISS YOU
OR IF I JUST MISS FEELING LOVED,
CARED ABOUT, AND IMPORTANT
YOU WALKED AWAY UNTOUCHED AND
UNBRUISED, STILL FEELING
COMPLETE OFF THE LOVE I GAVE YOU
WHILE I WAS LEFT TO CRY
I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND HOW MEN
LIKE YOU CAN CAUSE SO MUCH
DAMAGE OR EVEN WORSE, HOW WOMEN
SUCH AS MYSELF CAN EVEN STAND
IT.
I DON'T MISS YOU.
I MISFEELING LOVED.
YUP.
I DON'T WANT TO GO TO ANOTHER
ONE.
I JUSTED TO SAY THIS MEANS SO
MUCH JUST THEY GET TO STILL BE
AROUND.
THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
I MEAN, SINCERELY TRIBAL COUNCIL
WAS KIND OF A DISASTER FOR ME.
I WENT INTO THIS SORT OF
FIGHT-OR-FLIGHT MODE.
I GUESS I CHOSE FIGHT WHICH
DIDN'T NECESSARILY HAVE THE
OUTCOME I WANTED EVEN THOUGH I
DID STAY IN THE GAME.
MY TENDENCY TO GET INTO AN
ANXIOUS DEBATE MODE WASN'T
HELPFUL AND I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
TURN ON THE COOL, MELLOW
COCHRAN, INSTEAD OF THE KIND OF
ANTSY, PARANOID, NERD KID I
THINK I'VE WITHIN THE LAST FEW
DAYS.
I MEANT EVERYTHING I SAID.
I'M HAPPY TO CHANGE.
HOWEVER YOU THINK I CAN GET HELP
THE TRIBE.
I JUST WANT TO THANK YOU ALL.
WE'RE GLAD TO STILL HAVE YOU
HERE.
TONIGHT WE DECIDED WE'RE
GOING TO LET COCHRAN TRY TO
REDEEM HIMSELF.
I REALLY IDENTIFY WITH HIS
PASSION TO PLAY THIS GAME.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, HE NEEDS
TO UNDERSTAND THAT IF YOU DON'T
PUT IN THE EFFORT AROUND CAMP
AND YOU DON'T PUT IN THE EFFORT
IN THE CHALLENGES, THEN YOU
MIGHT BE THE NEXT ONE TO GO.
I'M ACTUALLY EXCITED FOR THE
NEXT CHALLENGE.
ME, TOO.
THE CHALLENGES ARE GOING TO
BECOME A LITTLE MORE DIFFERENT.
ONCE THEY'RE A COMBINATION OF
PHYSICAL, MENTAL--
THIS IS WHERE COCHRAN CAN
SHINE.
AND EVEN JIMMY,UN?
I THINK HE IS ACTUALLY PRETTY
GOOD WITH THE PUZZLES AND HE'S
PRETTY SMART.
WE GOTTA KEEP JIMMY AROUND.
I THINK HE'S AN AWESOME WORKER
WHICH IS REALLY GOOD.
YEAH, WE SHOULD TRY, US
THREE, MEADE UP TOMORROW.
WE NEED TO DO THAT.
FOR SURE.
YEAH, I REALLY DO LIKE OZZY A
LOT.
I THINK AN ALLIANCE WITH OZZY
COULD BE THE BEST BET TO STAY
STRONG PHYSICALLY, BUT OZZY'S
PLAYED THE GAME BEFORE, AND HE'S
GOING TO HAVE TO WIN IT JUST AS
MUCH AS WE ARE.
SO I HAVE TO WATCH HIM LIKE A
HAWK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT FELT LIKE YOU HAD MY BACK THE
FIRST DAY WHEN EVERYBODY WAS
LIKE TRUE COACH AND I WAS JUST
SITTING THERE AND YOU HELPED ME
OUT.
ARE YOU SERIOUS IN YOU'RE
JUST GOING TO LEAVE HIM OUT
THERE?
INITIALLY THINGS DIDN'T LOOK
GOOD FOR THE DRAGON SLAYER.
RIGHT ON THE BAT I'M ALREADY ON
THE OUTS WITH MY TRIBE.
HOW MUCH, I FEEL LIKE I HAVE
BEEN GIVEN A SECOND CHANCE.
NOW I HAVE A SOLID ALLIANCE WITH
RICK, SOPHIE, BRANDON, AND
ALBERT.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO FRIEND, YOU
CAN NEVER HAVE TOO MANY, AND
EDNA, SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
HOHELPED ME ON THE FIRST DAY, SO
MAYBE I'M JUST A BIG FOOL BUT
SHE SEEMS LIKE A GENUINELY NICE
PERSON.
I WOULD REALLY LIKE TO KNOW WHO
HAS THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
I DO YOU REALLY THINK CHRISTINE
FOUND IT WITHOUT ANY CLUES?
SHE WAS DIGGING FOR HOURS OUT
THERE.
WHAT ABOUT TODAY.
NOBODY WAS DIGGING.
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN DIGGING
BECAUSE I, THEY MIGHT HAVE FOUND
IT.
THEY'RE VERY TIGHT, TOO, IF YOU
HAVEN'T NOTICED.
WHO?
STACY AND CHRISTINE.
I THINK MY PLACE IN THE TRIBE IS
PROBABLY THE BOTTOM.
I'M NOT ONE OF THE PHYSICALLY
STRONGEST GIRLS IN THE TRIBE SO
I NEED TO ALIGN MYSELF WITH A
STRONGER MALE PLAYER AND, COACH,
I THINK HE'S A STRONG PLAYER.
HE HAS A HISTORY OF PLAYING
WELL, SO I WANTED TO SOLIDIFY MY
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM.
I'M ONE OF THE SMALLER FEMALES.
LISTEN, YOU WANNA KEEP THE
TRIBE STRONG BUT TO ME, LOYALTY,
I THINK, IS THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING.
THANK YOU.
LOYALTY SOMETIMES OUTWEIGHS
STRENGTH IN THIS GAME.
SO IT'S MY JOB TO PROTECT HER.
SO ARE YOU SOILED WITH ME?
ABSOLUTELY.
I FEEL LIKE I CAN TRUST YOU.
WELL, I'M STUPID IN THIS
GAME.
I'M THE BIGGEST FOOL IN THIS
GAME BECAUSE I'M ALWAYS HOPEFUL
THAT I WILL FIND SOMEBODY OUT
HERE THAT WILL PLAY HONORABLY.
SO WE'RE TOGETHER FOR SURE?
FOR SURE.
THIS IS ALL PART OF THE NEW
ERRAV COCHRAN.
IT'S THE COCHRAN THAT CUTS
COCONUTS WITHOUT BEING ASKED TO
DO SO.
MY MOM'S GOING TO HAVE MIXED
FEELINGS ABOUT THE NEW COCHRAN.
SHE'LL BE THRILLED I'M TAKING
INITIATIVE AND DOING WORK BUT
THE FIRST THING SHE SAID WHEN
SHE FOUND OUT I WAS DOING
SURVIVOR, SHE SAID I DON'T WANT
YOU TO HANDLE A MACHETE WITHOUT
SUPERVISION.
NEW COCHRAN OPENS A COCONUT BY
HIMSELF AND WITH A MACHETE.
I NEED TO MAKE THEM THINK OF ME
LESS AS THE LIABILITY AND DRAIN
ON THE TRIBE AND MORE AS A
POTENTIAL SURVIVOR.
IT'S GREAT.
PART OF IT IS BECAUSE IT'S THE
FRUIT OF MY LABORS SO IT'S LIKE
A CHILD.
SO I'M DRINKING YOUR CHILD?
I APPRECIATE IT.
IT'S BECOMING PART OF YOU.
I'M CERTAINLY NEVER GOING TO
BECOME THE BIG PROVIDER.
I KNOW I'M NEVER GOING TO BE
OZZY.
I'M NEVER GOING TO BE KEITH.
I'M NEVER GOING TO BE JIM BUT I
CAN AT LEAST BE THE NEW COCHRAN.
BEING PART OF A WELL-OILED
MACHINE IS MORE ENJOYABLE THAT I
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
I'M JUST GOING TO GO DOWN
THERE AND DO A FLOAT-DOWN AND
MAYBE GET LUCKY AND GET
SOMETHING.
I'M PRETTY SURE THE IDOL IS
ALREADY ON THIS BEACH.
WE DON'T HAVE A CLUE YET AT THIS
POINT SO I'M JUST TRYING TO KEEP
MY EYES PEELED FOR ANY SORT OF
WEIRD SIGN THAT THERE MIGHT BE
IDOL PLACEMENT.
I'M THINKING SOMEWHERE UP IN A
TREE OR MAYBE HIDDEN IN A STUMP
SOMEWHERE.
CAN'T BE TOO SURE.
LET'S GO LOOK BACK THE OTHER
WAY.
LET ME LOOK DOWN IN THERE REAL
QUICK AND GAND SEE WHAT THAT'S
ALL ABOUT.
WHAT'S A ROCK DOING IN THE
MIDDLE OF A TREE?
ME THINKS ME FOUND SOMETHING.
THREE TIMES AROUND, YOU START
LEARNING WHAT TO LOOK FOR.
ROCKS IN TREES ARE A GOOD SIGN
THAT YOU'VE FOUND SOMETHING
GOOD!
OH, THIS IS A GREAT DAY.
FIND ANOTHER HIDING SPOT.
I'VE HAD ONE OF THESE LITTLE
GUYS IN MY POSSESSION BEFORE AND
I WAS STUPID ENOUGH TO THE TO
PLAY IT.
I REALLY SQUANDERED THE
OPPORTUNITY TO GET REALLY FAR
THIS THAT GAME.
I AM SURE AS HELL NOT EVER GOING
TO LET THAT HAPPEN THIS TIME BUT
I CAN'T LET ANYBODY KNOW THAT I
HAVE THE IDOL.
IF ANYBODY SENSES THAT I HAVE
THE IDOL, THERE'S A VERY STRONG
POSSIBILITY THAT THEY'RE GOING
TO TRY AND FLUSH IT OUT.
SO IF I CAN MAKE IT TO THE MERGE
AND I COULD USE IT IN AN
OPPORTUNE MOMENT, THIS MIGHT BE
MY TICKET TO THE WIN.
HOW YOU FEELING THIS MORNING?
AWESOME, HOW ABOUT YOU?
AWESOME.
I TRIED TO CUDDLE UP WITH YOU
LAST NIGHT, MAN?
REMEMBER WHEN I ASKED YOU IF YOU
WERE COLD?
NO.
I ASKED YOU.
DID YOU PUT SOMETHING OVER
ME?
YEAH.
I APPRECIATE THAT, DUDE.
I REALLY LIKE COACH.
I THINK HE'S A REALLY GOOD GUY
AND HE'S PLAYED THE GAME TWICE
WITH HONOR AND INTEGRITY, AND I
WANT TO PLAY THE SAME WAY.
BUT IN THE BACK OF MY MIND THE
WHOLE TIME, I'M THINKING TO
MYSELF, MAN, HOW, YOU KNOW, HOW
UNGODLY OR HOW MUCH OF A
HYPOCRITE DO I LOOK LIKE HAVING
MADE AN ALLIANCE WITH COACH AND
HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW THAT I'M
RUSSELL HANTZ' NEPHEW AND IT
JUST DIDN'T FEEL RIGHT.
I'VE KIND OF NOT DONE THAT, MAN.
LYING TO COACH IS TEARING AWAY
AT EVERYTHING I BELIEVE IN.
AND I'D RATHER PEOPLE KNOW ME
FOR ME.
YOU WANT TO SEE SOMETHING COOL?
WHAT'S THAT?
IT SAYS, "LIL HANTZ."
THAT'S WHY I WEAR THE SHIRT
ALL THE TIME.
WAIT, BUT THAT'S NOT YOUR
LAST NAME, IS IT?
YEAH, I'M RUSSELL HANTZ'S
NEPHEW.
KEEP THAT ON THE D.L.
SO I TAKE A WALK WITH BRANDON
AND HE TELLS ME THAT HIS UNCLE
IS MY NUMBER ONE NEMESIS RUSSELL
HANTZ.
MY JAW LITERALLY DROPS.
THAT'S CRAZY, MAN.
I MEAN, IT WAS LIKE,UN, THIS
CAN'T BE.
AND THEN I HAD A SINKING FEELING
IN MY STOMACH BECAUSE RUSSELL
HANTZ TOLD ME AS A MAN OF GOD,
AS ACARINE GAPE, WE'RE GOING TO
PLAY THIS GAME TOGETHER AND HE
VOTE MY ASS OFF THE NEXT TIME HE
COULD SO IT SCARED ME.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU, MAN, I
DON'T WANT TO BE PLAYED A FOOL
TWICE.
I TOOK A HUGE LEAP.
THE ONLY REASON I TOLD YOU IS
BECAUSE I MADE AN ALLIANCE WITH
YOU.
IF IT BITES ME IN THE BUTT I
STILL FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT BECAUSE
I LET YOU KNOW.
COACH PLAYED THE GAME WITH MY
UNCLE AND HE GAVE HIM HIS WORD
AND IT DIDN'T WORK OUT BUT I
DON'T PLAN ON STACK COACH IN THE
BACK.
MEAS IN MY ALLIANCE AND I'M A
MAN OF MY WORD.
YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP THAT
BETWEEN ME AND YOU?
ABSOLUTELY.
I'M NOT GOING TO SAY THAT TO
ANYBODY.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING BRANDON FROM
THE FIRST DAY BECAUSE I FELT
LIKE WE HAD A CONNECTION RIGHT
OFF THE BAT.
AND, CLEARLY, HE HAS NOTHING TO
GAIN BY TELLING ME THAT
INFORMATION.
SO I THINK THAT HE'S TRUE TO HIS
WORD.
SO LET'S PRAY.
OKAY, FATHER, WE THANK YOU
FOR THIS DAY.
WE THANK YOU THAT YOU HAVE
BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
IN JESUS' NAME, GIVE US
STRENGTH, AMEN.
AMEN.
LOVE YOU, BRO.
SO IT'S GOING TO GO ONE OF
TWO WAYS.
IT'S EITHER GOING TO BE COACH
WAY, DUPED ONCE AGAIN IN
"SURVIVOR" OR IT'S GOING TO BE
REDEMPTION FOR THE HANTZ FAMILY.
I HOPE IT'S THE LATTER.
I'M HUNGRY.
ME, TOO, WE'RE GONNA GO CATCH
A FISH.
LIKE THESE LITTLE GUYS ARE
JUST, LIKE, FLOATING AROUND
TAUNTING.
YOU NEED TOUCHABLE CHANNEL MY
INNER NATIVE AMERICAN SELF.
YES, WE'RE EXPECTING IT FROM
YOU.
IT'S DAY FOUR, WE'RE HUNGRY,
AND SO ME, OZZY, AND KEITH WE
WENT OUT ON A FISHING TRIP.
BYE, LADIES!
BYE.
WE'LL BE DOING LAUNDRY!
IT'S A LOT OF FUN TO HAVE THE
GUYS OUT THERE DOING THEIR THING
AND DON'T THINK IT HAPPENED BY
CHANCE.
I'M A WORLD POKER TOUR CHAMPION
SO I'M ALREADY THINKING A FEW
MOVES AHEAD.
UP TO THE AMASS AS MANY CHIPS AS
YOU CAN FOR THE COMING WEEKS AND
THE REST OF THE GAME SO THE
FISHING TRIP GAVE ME A CHANCE TO
PUT IN PLACE THE THREE-PLUS-2
PLAN-- THE THREE GUYS, ME,
KEITH, AND OZZY AS THE CORE,
UNTIL THE END.
AND THEN THE PLUS-TWO ARE THE
TWO GIRLS WE LIKE, WHICH ARE,
LEASE AND WHITNEY.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAVE A PRETTY
GOOD RELATIONSHIP WITH WHITNEY.
YEAH, WE GET ALONG PRETTY
WELL.
SHE'S A COOL CHICK.
SHE'S EASY TO GET ALONG WITH.
SO YOU GUY WITH THE THROUGH
OF US AND ELIAS AND WHITNEY?
YEAH, I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
AND IF ONE OF THEM HAS TO
GO--
I AGREE.
SORRY.
JIM HAS MADE THIS LITTLE
ALLIANCE OF THE FIVE THAT HE
WANTS TO GO TO THE MERGE.
AND HE REALLY DOESN'T SUSPECT
THAT ME AND OZZY WERE ALREADY
TALKING TO EACH OTHER WHICH IS
GREAT BECAUSE IT LETS HIM THINK
HE'S IN CONTROL
IT'S A NO BRAINER.
BECAUSE I DON'T SEE ANY OF THE
FIVE OF US FLIPPING.
DEFINITELY, ALL OF US TILL
THE END.
I LIKE THE PLAN WE HAVE IN
PLACE.
I'M THE ORCHESTRATOR OF THIS
PLAN.
I PUT THIS PLAN TOGETHER.
I'M ARCHITECT.
I FEEL AT THIS MOMENT THAT WE
HAVE THE NEXT THREE PEOPLE THAT
ARE GOING TO BE GOING HOME KIND
OF ALREADY SET.
OBVIOUSLY, COCHRAN, DAWN, AND
PAPA BEAR.
EACH FOR THEIR OWN IDEOSINK
RASEES OR WEAKNESSES.
NAY JUST DON'T FIT IN.
I MEAN, I'VE ALWAYS BEEN THE KID
THAT DOESN'T ALWAYS FIT IN AND
SO I KNOW HOW THAT FEELS AND I'M
PROBABLY THE LEAST OF THE COOL
KIDS.
I'M AT THE KYLE KIDS' TABLE BUT
I'M BARELY AT THE COOL KIDS'
TABLE.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE DONE AS GOOD OF
A JOB RIGHT NOW AS I CAN DO.
I THINK I MIGHT JUST GO GET
ME SOME COCONUT WHIZ GET HOME.
WHO WANTS A COCONUT.
IT'S HARD TO GET OUT, IS WHAT
I MEAN.
THAT'S GOOD COCONUT.
GUYS, WE'RE GOING TO GO FISH.
YEAH, I'M GONNA FISH.
AT HOME, I BARTEND AND I ALSO
PLAY ON A PROFESSIONAL WOMEN'S
FOOTBALL LEAGUE.
IT'S FULL TACKLE.
WE HIT AS HARD AS THE GUYS SO
THEY THINK I'M A PRETTY TOUGH
CHICK.
I'LL TAKE THE COUNTRY BOY
WEAPON.
I AM KIND OF A TOMBOY SO IF
YOU SEE ME AT CAMP I'M RIGHT IN
THERE WITH THE GUYS DOING ALL
THE DIRTY WORK.
ROW?
WE'RE GONNA SWIM.
SWIM OUT THERE?
THE HARDEST PART OF THE GAME
IS THE SOCIAL ASPECT.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE THICK KING.
YOU CAN'T BE A LITTLE PRINCESS.
YEAH, ARE YOU GETTING NAKED.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE JUST GETTING
IN YOUR UNDERWEAR, BRO.
I DON'T SEE MYSELF AS A
GIRLIE-GIRL.
GUYS SEE ME AS JUST A STRONG,
SOLID PERSON AND I THINK THAT'S
GOING TO HELP ME IN THIS GAME.
THERE'S A PARTICULAR PERSON I
REALLY DON'T LIKE IN THIS GAME,
AND HER NAME IS MIKAYLA.
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE AROUND
HER.
YOU COULD TELL THE WAY SHE ACTS,
"I'M GOING TO BE A MODEL," AND
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
I CALL HER PARVATI, BECAUSE
SHE'S USING HER SEDUCTIVE WAYS
AND HER YOUNG GIRL ATTITUDE TO
KIND OF GET PEOPLE IN AND GET
ATTENTION.
IT'S THE ONES THAT ARE GOOD
LOOKING AND SEDUCTIVE THAT YOU
WANT TO GET RID OF.
BEING A MARRIED MAN, I HAVE TO
STAY AWAY INTEREST THAT KIND OF
STUFF.
I'VE MADE SOME PRETTY BAD
DECISION IN THE PAST, BUT I
SWEAR TO YOU, I WILL GET HER
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
AIN'T NO CHICK IN THIS WORLD
GETTING IN THE WAY OF ME, MY
FAMILY, AND A MILLION DOLLARS.
EVER.
AT THE LAST CHALLENGE, JEFF
TOLD US THAT THERE'S A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE IN CAMP.
NOBODY IS LOOKING FOR IT, SO I
DECIDED TO SEE IF I CAN FIND
THIS CLUE.
WHETHER THERE'S A TARGET ON MY
BACK, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I WOULD FEEL MORE
COMFORTABLE IF I HAD IT IN MY
POCKET.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE IDOL.
SAME HERE.
YEAH.
I THINK CHRISTINE HAS IT.
YOU DO?
YEAH.
IF SHE DO HAVE IT, SHE DIDN'T
TELL ME SHE HAD IT.
ONE PARTICULAR TREE LOOKED
VERY INTERESTING, AND IT HAD A
LOT OF INS AND OUTS AND CREVICES
AND LITTLE HIDING AREAS.
OH, MY GOD!
OUT OF THE CORNER OF MY EYE
SOMETHING LOOKED JUST OUT OF
PLACE.
A STICK WOULDN'T GROW IN THIS
ONE PARTICULAR AREA.
I SAID, THAT'S SO WEIRD.
AND I WENT BACK TO LOOK AT IT,
AND I FOUND THE CLUE.
"IT'S DEFINITELY NEAR THE
JUNGLE.
SOMEWHERE BY THE BEACH.
THE IMPORTANT THING TO REALIZE
IT IS JUST BARELY OUT OF REACH."
I'M FREAKING OUT.
I HAVE TO-- I HAVE TO FOCUS.
I HAVE TO REFOCUS.
BECAUSE NOW I HAVE THIS CLUE,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
DO I TELL THEM?
DO I NOT TELL THEM?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
UPOLU GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW SAVAII TRIBE.
SEMHAR VETED OUT AT THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
UPOLU, YOU WALKED IN AND
EVERYBODY HAD SOMETHING IN THEIR
MOUTH.
YOU'RE PUTTING IT BACK IN RIGHT
NOW, EVEN AS I'M ASKING YOU.
JEFF, WE FOUND SOME PAN DERA
THIS MORNING, AND IT'S MOST
DELICIOUS FRUIT.
Jeff: WHAT'S THE MESSAGE
YOU'RE CLEARLY TRYING TO SEND TO
SURVIVE.
THE TEAM THAT EATS PANDERA
TOGETHER STICKS TOGETHER AND
WINS TOGETHER.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO IT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
I WILL TAKE BACK THE IMMUNITY
IDOL.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, FOUR
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL RACE
TO UNWIND LONG RIBBONS FROM THE
VERY TALL POLE RELEASING A KEY
RING.
YOU WILL THEN USE THOSE KEYS TO
RELET'S OTHER FOUR TRIBE MEMBERS
WHO MUST THEN WORK TOGETHER
MOVING VERY HEAVY CRATES BACK
AND FORTH ACROSS A PLATFORM
UNTIL YOU CAN RELEASE THE
LARGEST ONE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET THEIR LARGE
CRATE ON THE FINISH PLATFORM
WINS IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
I KNOW SLEEPING ON BAMBOO IS NOT
THE NICEST WAY TO SPEND A NIGHT.
HOPEFULLY THE REWARD WILL MAKE
IT A LITTLE BETTER.
COMFORT!
OH, YEAH!
>>
( APPLAUSE ).
WHOOO!
Jeff: YOU'VE GOT PILLOWS,
BLANKETS, A HAMMOCK AND A MAP.
WORTH PLAYING FOR.
YES!
Jeff: IN ADDITION THE
WINNING TRIBE WILL RECEIVE A
CLUE TO THE LOCATION OF THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
UPOLU YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA MEMBER.
SITTING ONE PERSON OUT.
22 WHOIS IT GOING TO BE?
EDNA, DO YOU MIND?
WHATEVER YOU DECIDE AS A
TEAM.
WE'RE SITTING EDNA OUT.
Jeff: TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
WE'LL GIVE EVERYBODY ELSE A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, ON THE POLE FOR
SAVAII, COCHRAN, DAWN, WHITNEY,
AND ELYSE.
ON THE POLE FOR UPOLU, STACEY,
SOPHIE, CHRISTINE, AND MIKAYLA.
HERE WE GO!
GIRLS, WE GOT THIS.
Jeff: FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU'VE GOT TO UNTIE THE FOUR
KNOTS AND THEN START WORKING
TOGETHER.
UPOLU OFF TO A FAST START.
THESE RIBBONS ARE BRAIDED ON
THIS POLE.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
UNBRAID THEM.
KEEP GOING, RUN, RUN, RUN.
Jeff: SAVAII HAVING
TROUBLE.
WORK GIRLS, YOU'RE DOING
GREAT.
Jeff: UPOLU WORKING WELL
TOGETHER.
OVER COCHRAN.
COCHRAN GETTING CAUGHT UP IN
A RIBBON.
PULL ON OUT, COCHRAN, PULL IT
OUT.
Jeff: UPOLU WITH A BIT OF A
LEAD IN THIS FIRST STAGE, TRYING
TO RERELEASE A KEY.
UNDER!
GO!
Jeff: UPOLU HAS THE KEY.
STACEY HAS IT.
STACEY'S GOT TO UNLOCK THE FOUR
OTHER TRIBEMEMBERS.
SAVAII STILL TRYING TO GET THEIR
KEY RELEASED.
FOCUS, GUYS.
YOU GUYS GOT IT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S IT!
Jeff: STACEY HAS HER TRIBE
UNLEASHED.
START WORK THE PUZZLE.
COME OGUYS!
LET'S GO, FELLAS.
KEEP GOING.
YOU GOT IT.
SHAKE IT, SHAKE IT!
THERE YOU GO.
Andy:
Jeff: DAWN HAS THE KEY FOR
SAVAII!
LET'S GO.
FULL OUT!
Jeff: DAWN NEEDS TO PICK UP
PACE!
THIS IS NOT A PICNIC!
ELYSE NOW WORKING TRYING TO
RELEASE HER TRIBEMATES FOR
SAVAII.
LET'S GO, BOYS.
NICE, GUYS!
Jeff: UPOLU WITH A BIG
LEAD.
SAVAII STILL STRUGGLING.
COME ON, GUYS, YOU'VE GOT IT.
ELYSE HAS HER TRIBE UNLEASHED.
START WORK THE PUZZLE.
YOU GOT IT, GUYS.
Jeff: SAVAII HAS SOME
CATCHING UP TO DO.
UPOLU OUT TO A QUICK LEAD ON
THIS PUZZLE.
THESE PIECES SLIDE.
YOU CANNOT LIFT THEM.
OR CARRY THEM.
OTHER SIDE, OTHER SIDE.
Jeff: UPOLU REALLY TAKING
THEIR TIME.
SAVAII IS FLYING THROUGH THIS
PUZZLE.
COME ON!
Jeff: SAVAII DOES NOT WANT
TO GO BACK TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
COME ON, LET'S GO!
PUSH!
Jeff: UPOLU NEED TO PICK UP
THE PACE.
QUICKLY, QUICKLY, QUICKLY.
Jeff: UPOLU JUST LOST A
HUGE LEAD.
SAVAII IS CATCHING UP.
YOU'VE GOT TO MANEUVER YOUR
LARGEST PIECE OUT THE BACK ON ON
TO YOUR PLATFORM.
TO THE RIGHT!
TURN THE BIG ONE OVER!
Jeff: SAVAII NOW IN THE
LEAD.
COME ON, GUYS!
Jeff: UPOLU'S GOT TO HUSTLE
NOW.
THEY ARE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
SAVAII HAS THEIR FINAL PIECE IN
PLACE.
GO!
COME ON!
Jeff: SAVAII WITH A HUGE
COME FROM BEHIND!
MOVE OVER.
Jeff: UPOLU HAS THEIR LAST
PIECE IN PLACE.
BUT IT IS TOO LATE.
SAVAII WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
A HUGE COMEBACK VICTORY.
SAVAII, CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU
( APPLAUSE )
WHOOO!
YA!
Jeff: IN ADDITION TO
IMMUNITY, YOU HAVE PILLOWS,
BLANKETS, A MAT, AND A HAMMOCK,
AND WHEN YOU GET BACK TO CAMP,
THERE WILL BE A CLUE HIDDEN
SOMEWHERE ON YOUR BEACH.
FIND THE CLUE.
IT MAY HELP YOU FIND THE IDOL.
COME GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD OUT.
YES!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, UPOLU,
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
YOUR TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO THAT'S GOING TO BE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP, SEE YOU AT
TRIBAL.
WE WERE REALLY OVER-CONFIDENT
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU GET TOO COCKY AND YOU GET
KNOCKED OFF YOUR PEDESTAL SO NOW
WE HAVE TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT AND
I WILL MAKE SURE MIKAYLA GOES
HOME TONIGHT.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THE WOMEN
REALLY KICKED ASS TODAY.
REALLY DID A GREAT JOB.
YOU GUYS, DID, TOO.
THAT WAS NOT EASY.
WE LOST THE CHALLENGE TODAY AND
THE REWARD.
IT STARTED OUT WELL, BUT THE
GUYS WERE KIND OF JUST, YOU
KNOW, WALKING AND I THINK THEY
COULD HAVE HAD QUICKER FEET.
SO NOW WE HAVE TO VOTE SOMEBODY
OUT.
I JUST HOPE IT'S NOT ME GOING
HOME TONIGHT.
HERE'S WHAT I SAY, GUYS-- I
THINK WE OUGHT TO GO THREE,
THREE, AND THREE.
THREE, THREE, AND THREE.
THEY'RE GOING TO VOTE THREE.
WE SPLIT OUR VOTES, THREE FOR
STACEY, THREE FOR CHRISTIE.
WE NEED TO FLUSH THE IDOL IT IF
THE IDOL IS OUT THERE.
WE NEED TO PUT THREE VOTES TO
CHRISTINE BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
FORGOTTEN WHAT CHRISTINE SAID ON
DAY ONE, "COACH IS A TEMPORARY
PLAYER."
THAT PISSED ME OFF AND I HAVEN'T
FORGIVEN HER FOR RUNNING AROUND
LOOKING FOR THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
CHRISTINE AND STACEY ARE THICK
AS THIEVES.
EDNA IS TOTALLY LOYAL.
THESE ON A NEED-TO-KNOW BASIS.
I'LL TELL HER AT THE LAST
SECOND, "VOTE FOR STACEY."
I FEELEATE.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
ALL RIGHT.
JUST ALL RIGHT?
NO, I'M ALL RIGHT.
BETTER NOT BE JUST ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOT MY DOUBTS.
ABOUT WHO?
MIKAYLA.
BECAUSE I'M FAITHFUL TO MY WIFE
IT MAKES ME FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE
BEING AROUND HER A LOT OF TIMES.
INTERESTING.
I RESPECT THAT, MAN.
I RESPECT THAT.
I HAVE A BAD FEELING.
ALL I KEEP THINKING ABOUT IS
PARVATI, PARVATI, PARVATI.
SHE SCREWED MANY A MAN.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
AND BEING STRONG LIKE THAT,
LIKE SHE IS, JUST, YOU KNOW, I'M
GOING WITH THE TEAM, WHAT'S BEST
FOR US, BUT I THINK THAT'S OUR
BEST BET.
MIKHAIL'S OUR STRONGEST
FEMALE PLAYER BUT BRANDON HAS A
WIFE AND FAMILY AND I THINK SHE
MAKES HIM UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOUNG, GOOD-LOOKING GIRL.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT TO VOTE HER OFF IMMEDIATELY,
COME ON.
I JUST THINK THAT HE HAS DEMONS
THAT WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT
HE'S FACING ON A DAILY BASIS.
WE'VE GOT TO GET HER OUT OF
THIS GAME.
SHE'S NOT TO BE TRUSTED.
SHE NEEDS TO GO FIRST.
FOR SOME REASON OR OTHER,
BRANDON WANTS TO VOTE OUT
MIKAYLA.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HIS DEAL IS.
MAYBE BRANDON IS THREATENED BY
MIKAYLA BECAUSE SHE'S A STRONG
WOMAN AND IF THAT'S THE CASE, IT
WORRIES ME BECAUSE I THINK I'M
QUITE STRONG AS WELL.
WE'RE GOING TO GO--
MIKAYLA.
MIKAYLA OUT.
OUT.
TRUTHFULLY, I THINK MIKAYLA
RIGHT NOW WOULD VOTE CHRISTINE
IF WE TOLD HER TO.
I JUST FEEL IT.
I DO THINK WE NEED HER IN THE
CHALLENGE.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING I'M
THINKING ABOUT.
WHAT COULD THEY POSSIBLY BE
TALKING ABOUT WHAT'S MESSED UP
IS EDNA IS OVER THERE WITH NO
PROBLEM.
CHRISTINE IS NOT GOOD IN
CHALLENGES AND MIKAYLA IS.
HERE SHE COMES.
MIKAYLA, CAN YOU GIVE US A
LITTLE BIT OF PRIVACY?
OH, HERE'S STACEY.
I'M JUST GOING TO WALK THIS WAY.
I'M GETTING MY BAG.
I THINK EVERYONE'S PARANOID
RIGHT NOW.
WHAT'S COACH'S DEAL?
COACH IS FLIPPING OUT RIGHT
NOW.
I DON'T THINK HE TRUSTS ANY ONE
OF THE GIRLS RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T THINK HE TRUSTS YOU,
YOU, HER.
IT'S LIKE A MAD SCRAMBLE
RIGHT NOW, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
THEY THINK I'M NOT TRUSTABLE.
I'M LIKE, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
BUT I'M LIKE YOU'VE GOT TO BE
KIDDING ME.
DO YOU--
WHAT WERE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST PACKING JUST IN CASE.
WHAT WERE THEY SAYING?
I THINK THEY WERE TALK MAYBE
ABOUT SOPHIE TO BEGIN WITH.
NO, SOPHIE WAS OVER THERE,
TOO.
OH.
YOUR MESSING UP YOUR STORY
REALLY BIG TIME.
SO GET IT STRAIGHT--
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE STORY
IS.
WE'RE JUST ABOUT READY TO
LEAVE FOR TRIBAL, AND I HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON.
I MEAN, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO VOTE
OFF THE WEAK, SO I WAS LEANING
MORE TOWARDS EDNA, BUT NOW, IT
MIGHT BE ME FOR ALL I KNOW.
>>
WHO ARE YOU GOING FOR?
MIKAYLA.
DO YOU THINK SHE'S A BIGGER
THREAT THAN ANYBODY RIGHT NOW?
SHE'S VERY GOOD.
LET ME KNOW WHICH I WILL VOTE--
YOU HAVE TO KEEP YOUR EYES
OPEN.
YUP.
I JUST SAY VOTE FOR THE
PERSON WHO YOU THINK IS THE
BIGGEST THREAT IN THIS GAME.
BRANDON TOLD ME TO VOTE FOR
MIKAYLA, AND, HONESTLY, IT
CONFUSED ME.
WHY MIKAYLA?
IT MAKES ABSOLUTELY NO SENSE
WHATSOEVER.
IF WE DON'T AGREE WITH THEM,
IT WILL BE ONE OF OUR HEADS ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
I FEEL LIKE ONE OF OUR HEADS
IS ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK RIGHT
NOW.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT MYSELF RIGHT
I HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
CLUE AND I THINK MY HEART SAYS
YOU BETTER START LOOKING.
WE GOTTA LOCK IT DOWN NOW
BECAUSE THERE'S STILL CONFUSION.
RIGHT NOW, YOU WANT TO DO--
MIKAYLA.
PERIOD.
MIKAYLA MORE THAN CHRISTINE?
LET'S START OUT WITH A BANG.
I WOULD LOVE TO DO CHRISTINE
INSTEAD.
STASEY AND CHRISTINE JUST
TOLD ME THEY'RE VOTING MIKAYLA.
I HATE TO DO THIS TO PEOPLE BUT
I JUST WALKED UP TO COACH, AND I
LIED TO HIM.
IF CHRISTINE AND STACEY VOTE FOR
MIKAYLA IT'S BECAUSE I TOLD THEM
TO.
LOOK, I DON'T LIKE MIKAYLA.
I DON'T TRUST HER.
SHE'S GOT EVERY GUY AROUND HERE
WRAPPED AROUND HER FINGER BUT
ME, AND IT'S JUST NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
MIKAYLA WILL BE GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
THAT'S SO STUPID.
THESE PEOPLE ARE AMATEURS.
CRAZY.
I HEAR THAT CHRISTINE AND
STASE REGOING TO VOIGHT FOR
MIKAYLA AND THAT BUGS THE HECK
OUT OF ME BECAUSE SHE'S DONE
NOTHING WRONG BUT BRANDON WANTS
TO CONTROL THE SITUATION AND IF
HE WANTS AN OUTCOME, HE'S
WILLING TO RISK X, Y, AND Z TO
GET THAT OUTCOME.
IT DOESN'T NEED TO BE LIKE THIS,
BY THE WAY.
YEAH.
THIS GAME IS SIMPLE-- YOU
FIND PEOPLE THAT ARE LOYAL TO
YOU AND THAT'S IT.
THAT'S JUST SIMPLE.
YOU'RE LOYAL OR YOU'RE DISLOYAL.
I HOPE AND PRAY THE SIX PEOPLE,
I HAVE ALIGNED MYSELF WITH HAVE
THE CHARACTER I HAVE JUDGED THEM
FOR.
IF NOT THERE'S GOING TO BE AN
ASS-WHIPPING AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH AND
APPROACH THE FLAME.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE
YOU, WITH A SLIGHT EXCEPTION OF
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S START BACK AT
THE BEGINNING.
FIRST IMPRESSIONS.
BRANDON.
DO YOU THINK YOU MADE A GOOD
FIRST IMPRESSION ON THIS GROUP?
YES.
I DO.
YOU KNOW, I'M A HARD WORKER.
I'M POLITE WITH EVERYBODY,
TRYING TO MAKE FRIENDS.
I'M PRETTY SURE I MADE A GOOD
IMPRESSION ON EVERYBODY.
Jeff: COACH, YOU PLAYED
THIS GAME A COUPLE OF TIMES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THE FIRST
IMPRESSION OF YOU WAS?
AFTER LOSING THE FIRST
CHALLENGE I THOUGHT MY
IMPRESSION WAS PRETTY BAD SO
THERE WAS A LINE BEING DRAWN
EARLY ON THAT I FELT.
AND SO BEFORE WE STARTED WALKING
TO TRIBAL TONIGHT, I HAD HEARD
THAT CHRISTINE AND STACEY WANTED
TO VOTE OUT MIKAYLA.
AND DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE I'M
CRAZY BECAUSE COACH IN TRIBAL
JUST LAYS EVERYTHING OUT ON THE
TABLE.
OKAY.
DID I TALK TO YOU?
I DIDN'T TALK TO YOU ABOUT
THAT.
YOU GUYS DID NOT TALK TO ME
ABOUT THAT.
OKAY.
BECAUSE YOU GUYS HAVE NOT
TALKED STRATEGY TO ME SINCE DAY
ONE.
EXACTLY BUT WHAT YOU SAID WAS
NOT TRUE.
I NEVER MENTIONED MIKAYLA'S
NAME.
GO AHEAD.
WITHOUT BEING INTERRUPTED.
AS I SAID, THE GLOVES ARE OFF
AND LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
Jeff: SO GLAD YOU'RE BACK,
COACH.
IT'S GREAT TO BE BACK.
"SURVIVOR "IS A SIMPLE GAME.
YOU FIND PEOPLE THAT ARE LOYAL
AND YOU TRY TO STICK WITH THOSE
PEOPLE.
I'LL TELL YOU THE TRUTH RIGHT
NOW, I DON'T WANT TO I DON'T
WANT MIKAYLA GOING HOME TONIGHT
PUTTING A BIGGER TARGET ON MY
BACK.
Jeff: MIKAYLA, DOES IT MAKE
YOU A LITTLE NERVOUS THAT THERE
MIGHT BE TWO PEOPLE TALKING
ABOUT GETTING RID OF YOU?
OF COURSE IT MAKES YOU
NERVOUS.
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR NAME TO COME
UP.
LIKE COACH SAID, WE DON'T WANT
TO BE DOWN WHEN THE MERGE COMES.
I'M LIKE I DON'T GET IT.
Jeff: STACEY COACH JUST
THREW IT OUT THERE SAYING YOU
AND CHRISTINE ARE LOOKING TO
VOTE OUT MIKAYLA.
I NEVER TALKED TO HIM.
HIS HONESTY AND LOYALTY JUST
FAILED.
I DIDN'T SAY THEY TALKED TO
ME.
WHERE DID YOU GET IT FROM
THEN?
I NEVER EVEN MENTIONED THE
NAME MIKAYLA SO FROM WHOM IT IT
IT DID YOU HEAR THAT FROM,
MR. HONESTY.
FROM WHOM?
AS I REMEMBER DOWN, GUY
SIMMER DOWN WHAT?
HE'S THROWING OUT ACCUSATIONS
THAT HE CAN'T FOLLOW THROUGH ON.
FOR THE RECORD, NOT TO BE
FACT CHECK GUY, BUT I'M GOING TO
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW I DIDN'T TELL
COACH YOU WERE VOTING FOR
ANYBODY BECAUSE YOU NEVER TOLD
ME.
BUT IF YOU'RE GOING TO QUESTION
THE IDEA OF LOYALTY THINK ABOUT
HOW YOU'RE GOING ABOUT THAT
BECAUSE HIM NOT SAYING WHO TOLD
HIM THAT IS HIM DEMONSTRATING
LOYALTY.
AND I THINK A SOURCE OF
PARNOTICE AJEFF, WAS THE WHOLE
IDEA OF THE IDOL AND IF SOMEBODY
DID FIND THE IDOL, HOW WOULD WE
HANDLE IT?
I THINK THAT WAS THE RAINDROP
THAT STARTED THE MONSOON, SO TO
SPEAK.
Jeff: COACH WAS THERE A LOT
OF TALK RIGHT OFF THE BAT OF DO
WE LOOK FOR THIS AS A GROUP OR
DID YOU SEE PEOPLE SCATTERING
ABOUT?
I KNOW CHRISTINE LOOKED FOR
IT THE FIRST DAY AND I SAW TODAY
CHRISTINE LOOKING LIKE SHE WAS
GOING TO DIG IN A COUPLE PLACES.
Jeff: CHRISTINE HE JUST
THREW YOU UNDER THE BUS FOR THE
SECOND TIME.
HE'S GOOD AT THAT.
Jeff: DOES IT MAKE YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE?
FIRST HE SAYS YOU WANT TO VOTE
OUT MIKAYLA?
SECOND HE SAID YOU WERE LOOKING
FOR THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
HE'S THREATENED BY ME.
IT'S APPARENT.
Jeff: DO YOU THINK ANY OF
THIS STUFF WITH COACH MIGHT GO
BACK TO DAY ONE WHEN RIGHT OUT
OF THE GATE YOU SAID,
"MR. DRAGON SLAYER, YOU'RE
GONE."
I THINK SO.
I THINK-- YOU KNOW, I THINK HE
FEELS HURT THAT HE'S TEMPORARY.
I LOVE THIS GIRL.
LONG ISLAND ATTITUDE.
I LOVE IT.
Jeff: THERE'S ONE QUESTION
THAT HASN'T BEEN ASKED TONIGHT,
AND IT'S NOT A QUESTION I
HAVEN'T ASKED.
IT'S A QUESTION YOU HAVEN'T
ASKED, MIKAYLA, AND I'M SO
SURPRISED.
YOU'VE NOT ASKED CHRISTINE OR
STACEY IF THEY SAID IT.
IF YOU GO HOME TONIGHT, IT WILL
BE THE QUIETEST EXIT I'VE SEEN
IN A WHILE.
IS IT ON YOUR MIND?
NEVER.
NEVER DID I SAY I AM WRITING
YOUR NAME DOWN, EVER.
SO YOU CAN LOOK AT ME IN MY
EYES AND KNOW THE TRUTH OF THAT.
Jeff: SO-- YEAH, BRANDON
( SIZE )
I GOTTA COME CLEAN, MAN.
THE TRUTH IS THE TRUTH.
I KIND OF TOLD YOU GUYS TO VOTE
FOR MIKAYLA.
HE THE ONE WHO SAID VOTE FOR
MIKHAIL.
WE WAS NOT VOTING FOR MIKAYLA.
NO VOTES WERE GOING FOR
MIKAYLA.
YOU SEE HOW THE LIE CAME OUT.
I KNEW WHO I WAS VOTING FOR.
IT WASN'T MIKHAIL EVER.
BOOM.
Jeff: MIKHAIL AWELCOME TO
"SURVIVOR."
YOU'RE TELLING ME.
Jeff: CHRISTINE, THERE ARE
SO MANY FRACTIONS WITHIN THIS
BIG, HAPPY FAMILY.
HOW DO YOU YOU MAKE SENSE OF
EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED
TONIGHT?
I THINK THEY ARE A HAPPY
FAMILY.
I THOUGHT I WAS PART OF THAT.
BUT --
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT YOU
AREN'T.
ALBERT, YOU NEVER REALLY KNOW
WHO'S TELL THE TRUTH, WHAT'S A
PUT-ON, WHAT ISN'T.
DOES IT WORRY YOU THAT THIS
TRIBE IS IN SUCH DISARRAY.
I THINK WE'RE ALL GETTING A
LITTLE MORE INFORMATION THAN WE
BARGAINED FOR THIS EVENING BUT
IT'S GREAT WHEN THINGS COME TO
SURFACE AND PEOPLE KIND OF
REVEAL THEMSELVES BECAUSE A
PERSON'S PERSONALITY WILL CREEP
IN AND A PERSON'S CHARACTER WILL
CREEP IN A LITTLE BIT DESPITE
HOW HARD THEY TRY TO MASK THAT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, I HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
SOPHIE, YOU'RE UP.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
IF ANYBODY HAS THE
HIDDENIMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT
TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTE OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SOPHIE.
EDNA.
CHRISTINE.
STACEY.
THAT'S ONE VOTE EACH FOR STACEY,
EDNA, CHRISTINE, AND SOPHIE.
CHRISTINE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES CHRISTINE.
STACEY.
TWO VOTES STACEY.
CHRISTINE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CHRISTINE,
TWO VOTES STACEY.
STACEY.
WE'RE TIED, THREE VOTES
CHRISTINE, THREE VOTES STACEY,
ONE VOTE LEFT.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC"
CHRISTINE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
CHRISTINE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
WELL, WE'RE ONLY FIVE DAYS INTO
THIS GAME, AND ALREADY THE
BIGGEST OBSTACLE FOR THIS TRIBE
IS TRUST.
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU GUYS ARE
GOING TO HAVE TO WORK OUT OR
YOU'RE GOING TO BE COMING BACK
HERE A LOT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
AT SAVAII, THE PRESSURE IS ON
OZZY.
OZZY LOST HIS BOARD.
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL ANYONE
I HAVE THE IDOL.
HE'S UP TO SOMETHING.
I LIED BLATANTLY.
I THINK BRENDAN IS A DEVIOUS
JERK.
HE LETS THINGS GET TO HIM.
THIS IS A CONSTANT BATTLE
BETWEEN GOOD, EVIL, GOOD, EVIL.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED AT TRIBAL,
BUT I THINK COACH HAD A HEAVY
HAND IN THE VOTING PROCESS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT COACH HAD IN
MIND.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HIS PROBLEM
WAS.
BUT HE'S A TOOL.
HELLO!
EXCUSE ME.
WAKE UP.
I'M WITH YOU NOW.
Captioning brought to you
by Survivor Productions, CBS.
Captioned by Media Access Group
at WGBH