Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": SINCE DAY ONE, COACH
HAS BEEN THE DRIVING FORCE
BEHIND AN IMPENETRABLE ALLIANCE
OF FIVE.
WE'VE GOT RICK, BRANDON,
SOPHIE, ALBERT, AND YOU'VE GOT
MYSELF.
Jeff: AND HE ADDED EDNA AS
THE SIXTH.
I CAN'T LIE TO ANYBODY
ANYMORE.
Jeff: BUT BRANDON SHATTERED
ANY ILLUSIONS EDNA HAD ABOUT
MOVING UP IN THE PECKING ORDER.
BRANDON SAID THE OTHER FIVE
PEOPLE IN THE ALLIANCE HAVE
BASICALLY JUST TOLERATED ME.
Jeff: WE ARE MERGED.
AFTER THE TWO TRIBES MERGED,
THEY WERE DEAD EVEN.
AT THIS POINT, IT'S A
DEAD-LOCKED 6-6 VOTE.
YOU ARE THE MOST POWERFUL MAN
IN THE GAME.
Jeff: BUT COACH SOMEHOW
CONVINCED COCHRAN TO JUMP FROM
SIX AT THE OLD SAVAII TO SEVEN
IN HIS ALLIANCE.
WHO IS THE STRONGEST,
STRONGEST MAN ON EARTH THEY
CALLED HIM?
HERCULES.
YUP.
I'M HERCULES.
I CONVINCED COCHRAN HE WILL
BE THE MAN OF THE MATCH.
Jeff: KEITH, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
WITH THE NUMBERS ADVANTAGE THE
OLD UPOLU TRIBE PICKED OFF THE
OLD SAVAII TRIBE ONE BY ONE.
LEAVING OZZY, DAWN, AND WHITNEY
AT REDEMPTION ISLAND.
OH, MAN.
Jeff: WAITING TO BATTLE IT
OUT FOR A SHOT AT RETURNING TO
THE GAME.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THE SEVEN OF
YOU HAVE ACCOMPLISHED YOUR GOAL.
THE BAD NEWS-- NOWHERE LEFT TO
HIDE.
THIS GAME IS ABOUT TO CHANGE.
AND THERE WERE SEVEN.
WHOO-HOO.
WE HAVE ERADICATED ALL FORMER
SAVAII MEMBERS.
WE HAVE SEVEN LEFT AND WE'RE
ALL FAMILY SO NOW WE HAVE TO
START SENDING HOME SOME OF OUR
OWN.
WAS ANYBODY WORRIED TONIGHT
OR NOT REALLY?
NO.
COMING BACK FROM TRIBAL, AT
LEAST THE SENSE OF PARANOIA,
BECAUSE NOW PEOPLE HAVE IDEAS
FLOATING AROUND WHO IS FIVE,
SIR, AND SEVEN, AND WHO IS NOT
IN THAT TOP FOUR?
I'M DELUDED INTO THINKING I'M
SAFE.
LIKE I SAID AT TRIBAL, I'M
GOING TO STICK TO IT.
I'M HAPPY WITH MY DECISION, NO
VACILLATING, NO QUESTIONING.
TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS KIND OF
ALARMING TO ME BECAUSE IT WAS
MADE CLEAR I WAS THE PERSON THAT
WAS GOING IN SEVEN.
THANK YOU FOR ADOPTING ME INTO
YOUR FAMILY.
DOESN'T THIS FEEL GREAT?
IT FEELS LIKE WE'RE FINALLY--
LIKE WHEN THERE ARE SO MANY
PEOPLE HERE I HATE IT.
IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE WE'RE A
TRIBE.
AFTER SURVIVING ANOTHER NIGHT
I REALIZE THE FAMILY COULD TURN
ON ME AT ANY MOMENT SO I'LL
REALLY REEVALUATING WHAT I NEED
TO DO TO GET FURTHER IN THIS
GAME TO MAKE SURE I'M NOT TAKEN
OUT BY THE FAMILY.
GOSH, HELTER-SKELTER.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
I'VE BEEN A GOOD KID AND DONE
WELL IN SCHOOL BUT FIFTH GRADE
FOR WHATEVER REASON WAS KIND OF
MY RAMBUNCTUS PERIOD.
I WASSED TO CHANGE MY REPUTATION
AS A BROWN NOSER SO THE NASTIEST
THING I COULD THINK OF WAS TO
START PRANK CALLING PEOPLE.
I DIDN'T HAVE A GOOD IDEA OF HOW
SEX WORKED SO I WAS CALLING
THESE GIRLS AND SAYING THINGS
LIKE, "I THINK YOU'RE SO HOT.
I REALLY WANT TO TRADE SPERM
WITH YOU."
( LAUGHTER ).
I'M SORRY 72.
AND THEN I'D HANG UP AND
THINK THAT WAS A SUCCESSFUL
PRANK CALL.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT PERSONALITY
IS SOMETHING COCHRAN HAS GOING
FOR HIM OUT HERE.
WHEN I FIRST CAME HERE I FELT
KIND OF BAD FOR COCHRAN, BECAUSE
I FELT LIKE PEOPLE WERE BULLYING
HIM BUT I CAN SEE NOW WHY PEOPLE
GOT ANNOYED WITH HIM.
YOU KNOW, I GET FRUSTRATED BY
THE KIND OF AIR HE PUTS ON.
I THINK HE'S REALLY PROUD OF THE
MOVE HE MADE, AND I THINK HE
STILL THINKS THAT SOMEBODY WILL
TAKE HIM TO THE END.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
THERE HAS KIND OF ALWAYS BEEN
THIS CULT-LIKE QUALITY TO THE
UPOLU FAMILY.
JUST HEARING THE WORD "FAMILY"
OVER AND OVER YOU CAN'T HELP BUT
THINK OF CHARLES MANSON AND THE
MANSON FAMILY AND THE FAMILY
THAT CREATED SO MANY HEINOUS
MURDERS.
HOLY GOD, HELP US TO STAY
STRONG, STAY AWAY FROM
TEMPTATION, FATHER GOD, DON'T
GET ANGRY WITH EACH OTHER AND
WE'LL JUST STAY A FAMILY IN
JESUS' NAME, AMEN.
BRANDON IN PARTICULAR SEEMS
ALMOST OBSESSIVELY DEVOUT, TO
THE POINT WHERE IT SEEMS LIKE
HE'S TRYING TO SUPPRESS
SOMETHING A LOT MORE SCARY.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SHARON
TATE IN THIS SCENARIO, AND I
NEED SOME SORT OF PLAN OR ELSE
I'M GOING TO BE EXTERMINATED.
I'M GOING TO BE GIVEN THE POISON
KOOL-AID AND MEET MY UNTIMELY
DEMISE.
GOOD MORNING, GUYS.
BASICALLY WHAT I WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT IS I REALIZE THAT MY NAME
IS PROBABLY BEING FLOATED AROUND
TO BE THE NEXT PERSON VOTED OUT
OF THE TRIBE, AND IT MAKES SENSE
BECAUSE I'M NEW HERE BUT I MADE
A BIG SACRIFICE TO KIND OF
CHANGE MY GAME, AND I FEEL LIKE
THE UPOLU TRIBE DID BENEFIT FROM
IT.
SO BASICALLY ALL I'M ASKING IS
FOR THE DEBT TO BE PAID BACK
JUST BY SAVING ME FROM ONE
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU TO PROMISE ME
FINAL FOUR OR EVEN FINAL FIVE.
I WOULD JUST REALLY, REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
AND IT IS MY BIRTHDAY IN THREE
DAYS SO I'D LOVE TO CELEBRATE MY
BIRTHDAY WITH ALL OF YOU.
IF YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT I'M
WILLING TO LEAVE AND LET YOU ALL
DISCUSS.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, COCHRAN.
COCHRAN SAID, "I KNOW A LOT
OF YOU FEEL INDEBTEDDED TO ME."
I DON'T FEEL INDEBTEDDED TO YOU.
SCREW YOU.
HE MADE AN AWFUL MOVE.
HE SHOULD HAVE STUCK WITH HIS
TRIBE.
I'LL BE HONEST, GUYS, I'M NOT
REALLY GOING TO SAY MUCH BECAUSE
I THINK HE MAKES A VALID POINT
BUT IT'S NOT MY OPINION.
IT'S THE OPINION OF US FIVE.
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO DO I'LL
SUPPORT.
I AGREE WITH ALBERT, HE
SACRIFICED SO MUCH FOR US AND I
WANT IT TO BE A GROUP DECISION.
I WOULD SAY THAT I WOULD VOTE
FOR SWITCHING IT TO KEEP COCHRAN
HERE ANOTHER DAY.
YES, I THINK HE MADE BIG
MOVES BUT I FEEL JUST AS
INDEBTED TO EDNA AS I DO TO
COCHRAN.
SO IF THIS IS A DEMOCRACY, MY
VOTE IS FOR COCHRAN.
ALBERT AND I SEE WE DO OWE
COCHRAN ANOTHER DAY IN THIS
GAME.
IF WE COULD JUST PULL ONE MORE
VOTE TO KEEP COCHRAN.
WE'VE GOTTEN DOWN TO THE SEVEN.
EVERYBODY IS FIGHTING TO BE
STANDING AT THE BITTER END.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
OZZY, DAWN, AND WHITNEY.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS KNOW THE
STAKES.
IN ORDER TO STAY IN THIS GAME,
YOU HAVE TO WIN TODAY'S DUEL.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU WILL
BALANCE CERAMIC DISHES ON THE
END OF A LONG, WOBBLY ARM.
THE MORE DISHES YOU STACK, THE
MORE DIFFICULT IT WILL BE TO
KEEP THEM STABLE.
WHEN YOUR DISHES FALL, YOU'RE
OUT OF THE DUEL.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING STAYS
ALIVE AND WILL CONTINUE THEIR
QUEST TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME
FOR A SHOT AT THE MONEY.
LOSERS ARE OUT OF THE GAME FOR
GOOD AND WILL BECOME THE THIRD
AND FOURTH MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY PICK UP
YOUR ARM AND PLACE IT.
FIRST DISH YOU'RE GOING TO PUT
ON IS A LARGE PLATE.
MAKE SURE YOU HAVE IT WHERE YOU
WANT IT.
GET COMFORTABLE WITH THAT ARM.
SEE WHAT THAT FEELS LIKE WHILE
YOU STILL HAVE A CHANCE TO
EXPERIMENT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S ADD A LARGE
BOWL.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
PLACE IT, THINK ABOUT THE DISHES
THAT ARE GOING TO GO ON TOP OF
IT.
AS THIS STACK GROWS, IT'S GOING
TO GET DIFFICULT.
DAWN YAWN, AND ALMOST COST HER
THIS GAME.
THEY'RE NOW STACKED NINE DISHES
HIGH.
WE'RE GOING TO ADD ANOTHER DISH.
YOU'RE GOING TO ADD A SMALL
PLATE.
THIS IS A MILLION-DOLLAR
DO-OR-DIE DUEL RIGHT HERE.
OZZY STARTING TO WOBBLE A
LITTLE.
NICE RECOVERY.
TIME TO ADD ANOTHER DISH.
YOU'RE GOING TO PLACE A LARGE
BOWL.
ANYBODY CAN WIN THIS GAME IF YOU
CAN JUST GET TO THE END.
DAWN LOSES HER STACK.
DAWN IS OUT OF THIS DUEL AND OUT
OF THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
SHE BECOMES THE THIRD MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
GREAT JOB, DAWN.
Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO ADD
THE 12th DISH, A LARGE
PLATE.
YOU SAW HOW FAST YOU CAN BE OUT
OF THIS.
DON'T LOSE YOUR FOCUS.
TIME TO ADD A SMALL BOWL.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
NICE JOB.
WHITNEY STARTING TO WOBBLE A
LITTLE.
WHITNEY LOSES HER STACK.
WHITNEY IS OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
OZZY STAYS ALIVE AND CONTINUES
HIS QUEST TO GET BACK IN THIS
GAME.
YOU JUST WANTED TO BREAK
THAT.
IT WAS A PLEASURE, LADIES.
IT WAS SUCH A PLEASURE.
Jeff: DAWN, WHAT'S THE
LESSON THAT YOU LEARNED ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF IN LIFE?
THAT ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE.
THAT ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
I MEAN, IT'S-- IT'S HONESTLY, I
MEAN, I THINK THAT'S GOING TO BE
FUEL FOR ME AND MY FAMILY AND MY
KIDS.
I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE IF ONE OF MY
KIDS SAYS, "HEY, I'VE GOT THIS
PIPE DREAM," I'M GOING TO SAY,
"LET ME HANG ON AND LET'S GO."
I HOPE THE PEOPLE I'M AROUND
WILL FEEL THIS ENERGY I FELT
FROM SEEING THE IMPOSSIBLE
BECOME POSSIBLE.
Jeff: DAWN, YOUR ADVENTURE,
SADLY FOR YOU, HAS COME TO AN
END.
BUT I GOT TO TAKE IT.
Jeff: IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO
GO.
YOU BECOME THE THIRD MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
BYE.
PROBST, I LOVE YOU.
Jeff: OOH.
PUT IT IN?
Jeff: PUT IT IN.
SORRY.
WHITNEY, WHAT WAS THIS ADVENTURE
ABOUT FOR YOU?
JUST PROVING THAT YOU CAN DO
THIS.
IT WAS AMAZING, AND IT WAS HARD
BUT YOU MAKE IT THROUGH IT AND
YOU PUSH THROUGH ON THOSE DAYS
THAT YOU DON'T THINK YOU CAN.
MY FAMILY IS GOING TO BE PROUD,
AND MY FRIENDS WILL BE PROUD,
AND SO I'M GOING TO BE PROUD.
28 DAYS IS A LONG TIME.
Jeff: WHITNEY, THIS PARENT
OF YOUR LIFE'S ADVENTURE HAS
COME TO AN END.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
YOU BECOME THE FOURTH MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
GOOD JOB.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
OZZY, YOU STAY ALIVE IN THIS
GAME.
YOU'RE ONE STEP CLOSER TO
GETTING BACK IN FOR A SHOT AT
THE MONEY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AWAIT YOUR NEXT OPPONENT.
SEE YOU GUYS.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
FROM THIS POINT ON, I'M EVEN
MORE EXCITED TO GO INTO THE
DUELS AND BEAT PEOPLE THAT ARE
MY ENEMIES IN THIS GAME.
I HAVE TO RELY ON MYSELF
WINNING, BUT THAT IS WHAT I DO
BEST, AND THAT'S THE WAY THAT I
WANT TO WIN THIS GAME.
I CAN SURVIVE OUT HERE ON
REDEMPTION.
I CAN KEEP GETTING STRONGER.
THIS IS MY HOME, REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
THIS IS HOW I'M PLAYING THE
SECOND HALF OF MY GAME AND
THERE'S NO ONE BETTER SUITED TO
BE OUT HERE THAN ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
WHAT'S ON YOUR AGENDA?
I WAS GOING TO GO FISHING BUT
COCHRAN WANTED TO GO AND WHEN IT
COMES TO FISHING, THREE IS
COMPANY BUT FOUR'S A CROWD.
DO YOU HAVE ANY CLOTHES TO
WATCH?
EDNA IS OUT THERE DOING THE
LAUNDRY AND THE FUNNY THING IS,
YOU KNOW, THIS IS "SURVIVOR" THE
ULTIMATE STRATEGY GAME.
THE FLAIRS MY ALLIANCE THINK
IT'S NOT OUTWIT, OUTPLAY,
OUTLAST.
THEY THINK IT'S OUTCLEAN,
OUTGATHER, OUTORGANIZE.
TO ME THIS GAME IS ABOUT DOING
WELL IN CHALLENGES, CREATING A
GREAT STRATEGY, AND PLAYING A
STRONG SOCIAL GAME.
SO THOSE ARE WHAT I'M FOCUSED
ON.
I'LL LEAVE THE HOUSEWORK TO
MARTHA STEWART.
AWESOME, MAN.
IT'S GOT TEETH SO BE CAREFUL.
WHAT DO I DO?
I'M AFRAID OF HURTING MYSELF.
YOU'RE WHAT?
BRANDON JUST CAUGHT THIS
GIANT, REALLY SCARY LOOKING FISH
THAT HAVE THESE KIND OF
INTIMIDATING-LOOKING FANG TEETH
AND I'M IN CHARGE OF HOLDING IT
BUT IT SEEMS TO HAVE SOME LIFE
IN IT SO I'M NERVOUS IT WILL
RESURRECT AND ATTACK ME.
BUT WHATEVER IT TAKES TO FEED
OUR TRIBE I'M WILLING TO PUT OUR
PLAINTIFF AND LIMB IN DANGER AND
BRANDON IS DOING AN AWESOME JOB
OF FISHING AND I'M HAPPY TO HELP
OUT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M PART OF THE
TEAM.
I DIDN'T PHYSICALLY CATCH IT,
BUT I'M PHYSICALLY HOLDING IT
AND I'LL BINGLY BE THE ONE TO
BRING IT BACK TO CAMP AND HIM
THE ONE THEY'LL HOIST ON THEIR
SHOULDERS.
EVERYBODY WORKED REAL HARD
TODAY, MAN.
I APPRECIATE YOU COMING OUT
THERE AND HELPING US.
I'M GLAD TO HELP.
THIS GUY WAS SO PATIENT.
HE WAS SITTING THERE...
BYE, EDNA.
BYE.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK SO.
ALBERT PROCEEDED TO LAY IN
THE HAMMOCK AND WATCH ME FOR TWO
HOURS WHILE I DID THE LAUNDRY,
AND WHEN I STEPPED AWAY FROM THE
LAUNDRY FOR ONE MINUTE, I COME
BACK TO THE FIRE BEING DOUSED
OUT, AND THE EMBERS ARE WET AND
YOU CAN'T GET THE FIRE STARTED
THAT EASILY.
OH, THAT WAS SO INFURIATING.
ALBERT DOES PRETTY MUCH NOTHING
EXCEPT LIE AROUND AND EAT FISH
AND WAIT FOR OTHER PEOPLE TO
WAIT ON HIM.
I DON'T THINK ALBERT HAS DONE
A DAY OF WORK IN HIS LIFE.
I THINK THAT BOTH HAS BEEN
HAND-CLOTHED, HAND-BATHED BY HIS
MOTHER SINCE HE WAS TWO.
HE JUST LITERALLY STAY ON THE
HAMMOCK FOR TWO HOURS AND SO NOW
I WAS LIKE THERE'S NO FIRE, THE
LAUNDRY IS NOT DONE AND ALBERT
HASN'T DONE ANYTHING.
HE LITERALLY SAT THERE.
ALBERT IS A KIND OF PRECIOUS
THING IN CAMP.
HE'S LIKE ONE OF THOSE BARBIE
DOLLS.
THEY LOOK CUTE BECAUSE THEY
DON'T DO DO ANYTHING AND SIT
THERE.
THAT'S WHY I CALL HIM PRINCE
ALBERT.
IT'S LIKE I'M THE PRINCE AND YOU
GUYS WORK FOR ME.
IT JUST KILLS ME.
TELL ME I'M BASICALLY NEXT
PERSON TO GO AFTER COCHRAN.
IS THAT STILL TRUE?
I THINK SO, YES.
WHY?
BECAUSE IT'S TIME TO START
PICKING EVERYBODY OFF ONE ON
ONE.
I KNOW, BUT WHY AM I NEXT?
I FOUND OUT I'M BASICALLY THE
NEXT PERSON TO GO AFTER COCHRAN
WHICH MAKES ME FEEL AS THOUGH I
AM PRETTY LOW ON THE TOTEM POLE.
I DEFINITELY HAVE TO SHAKE IT UP
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE SIXTH OR
SEVENTH IS NOT ACCEPTABLE FOR
ME.
DO YOU HAVE ANY SUGGESTIONS, ANY
IDEAS?
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN, COACH?
MY UNDERSTANDING IS WE'RE AT A
CONSENSUS THAT COOK RAN IS NEXT?
YES.
KEEPING EDNA AND COCHRAN WOULD
BE THE BEST THING FOR ME TO DO
BECAUSE THEY'RE NEVER GOING TO
VOTE ME OUT SO IT'S REALLY LIKE
A CATCH-22.
WHICH SIDE SHOULD I GO AT THIS
POINT.
DO I WANT TO HONOR MY WORD, BE A
MAN OF INTEGRITY, STICK WITH THE
FIVE OR DO I WANT TO GO ANOTHER
ROUTE?
NOTHING IS FOR SURE IN THIS GAME
YOU KNOW WHY WE'RE DOING THIS
THIS MORNING?
WHY?
TO CENTER YOU AND EMPOWER
YOU.
RIGHT?
YEAH.
ONE OF THE TWO OF US SHOULD
WIN IMMUNITY TODAY BECAUSE WE'RE
DOING THIS.
THERE'S THAT ONE PLAYER ON EVERY
TEAM THAT YOU GIVE EVERYTHING
TO.
IT'S WHY YOU TEACH OR COACH AND
IT'S WHY I PLAY "SURVIVOR" TO
FIND THAT ONE STUDENT THAT WANTS
TO LEARN.
SO I TOOK COCHRAN OUT TO DO
THI CHI.
I DO FEEL LIKE I OWE COCHRAN AND
I FEEL LIKE I OWE HIM SOME TYPE
OF HOPE GOING INTO THE
CHALLENGE.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT KIND OF
CHALLENGE IT'S GOING TO BE AND
MAYBE, YOU KNOW, HOPEFULLY IT
WILL EMPOWER HIM.
UP.
COACH, FOR ALL THE JOKES
ABOUT IT AND ALL THE JOKES
DIRECTED AT COACH, IT IS A
VALUABLE THING FOR ME TO DO.
USUALLY I HAVE ALL THESE
CONFLICTING GOALS BOUNCING
AROUND IN MY HEAD-- HOW DO I
CURRY FAVOR WITH BRANDON, HOW DO
I MAKE RICK LIKE ME, HOW DO I
MAKE COACH LIKE ME-- BUT NOW ALL
THE STRESS EXITED MY POURS.
ALL THAT WINS IS A SINGULAR
DRIVE TO WIN IMMUNITY AND I
THINK I CAN DO IT AFTER TODAY'S
SESSION.
YOU GOOD TO GO, MAN?
YES.
I'M JUST NERVOUS BUT I'LL GET
THERE.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YOU BET.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
SOPHIE, I'LL TAKE IT BACK AGAIN.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, I'M GOING
TO GIVE YOU A LITTLE "SURVIVOR:
SOUTH PACIFIC" DEJA VU.
THE FIRST STAGE, YOU WILL TOSS
SANDBAGS ATTEMPTING TO LAND THEM
ON TOP OF CRATES.
THE FIRST THREE TO GET A SANDBAG
ON EACH OF THEIR CRATES MOVES ON
TO THE FINAL ROUND WHERE YOU
WILL USE A LARGE SLINGSHOT TO
FIRE COCONUTS AT TARGETS.
FIRST PERSON TO KNOCK DOWN ALL
THEIR TARGETS WINS IMMUNITY, IS
SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER OF THIS
CHALLENGE WILL BE TREATED TO A
NICE "SURVIVOR" SPA AFTERNOON.
YOU'LL GO BACK TO CAMP WHERE YOU
WILL GET A CHANCE TO ENJOY A
BUSH SHOWER.
YOU'LL THEN HAVE A MASSAGE, WORK
OUT SOME OF THE CINCHES FROM 30
DAYS OUT HERE.
COULD BE JUST WHAT YOU NEED FOR
THESE LAST NINE DAYS.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
YEAH.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'LL DRAW
FOR SPOTS AND GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, THREE PEOPLE WILL
MOVE ON TO THE FINAL ROUND.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
TOSS.
COACH LANDS HIS FIRST ONE.
SOPHIE LANDS HER FIRST ONE.
BRANDON LANDS ONE.
EDNA LANDS ONE.
COCHRAN LANDS ONE.
ALBERT LANDS ONE.
COACH LANDS HIS SECOND BAG.
RICK LANDS ONE.
EVERYBODY HAS ONE BAG.
COACH HAS TWO BAGS.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A TOTAL OF
THREE.
OH!
Jeff: ALBERT HUNG ON THE
EDGE AND THEN FELL OFF.
COACH ON AND OFF.
SOPHIE LANDS HER SECOND BAG.
RICK LANDS HIS SECOND BAG.
SOPHIE, COACH, AND RICK EACH
HAVE TWO BAGS.
EVERYBODY ELSE HAS ONE.
ALBERT STICKS HIS SECOND.
BRANDON GIVES IT A GO.
ON AND OFF.
RICK IS ON AND OFF.
ALBERT NAILS IT.
ALBERT IS MOVING ON TO THE FINAL
ROUND.
WE ARE LOOKING FOR TWO MORE.
SOPHIE, OH!
WILL NOT STICK.
COCHRAN'S GOT HIS SECOND.
COCHRAN IS NOW BACK IN THIS.
YES!
Jeff: RICK LANDS HIS THIRD
BAG.
RICK HAS MOVED ON TO THE FINAL
ALONG WITH ALBERT.
ONE SPOT REMAINS.
IF SOPHIE, COCHRAN, OR COACH
LANDS A BAG RIGHT NOW, THEY MOVE
ON TO THE FINAL ROUND.
WILL IS THAT DO IT FOR COACH?
NO.
COCHRAN A LITTLE SHORT.
CAN SOPHIE DO IT RIGHT HERE?
AND SHE DOES!
SOPHIE MOVES INTO THE FINAL WITH
ALBERT AND RICK.
ALL RIGHT, FOR THE FINAL ROUND,
IT IS ALBERT, SOPHIE, AND RICK.
FIRST PERSON TO HIT ALL THREE OF
THEIR TARGETS WITH A COCONUT
WINS IMMUNITY AND MASSAGE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
YOU CAN ONLY GRAB ONE COCONUT AT
A TIME BUT YOU CAN GO AS FAST AS
YOU CAN MOVE.
EVERYBODY LOOKING TO GET THEIR
FIRST SHOT IN.
ALBERT JUST MISSES LOW.
SOPHIE JUST MISSES LOW.
RICK JUST MISSES LOW.
ALBERT CONNECTS WITH HIS FIRST
TARGET.
ALBERT WITH ONLY TWO TARGETS
LEFT.
RICK GET HIS FIRST TARGET.
SOPHIE, GOTTA GET IN THIS.
RICK HITS HIS SECOND TARGET.
GOOD JOB, RICK.
Jeff: RICK NOW WITH ONE
TARGET LEFT.
ALBERT JUST MISSES.
RICK COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
JUST SHORT.
ALBERT HITS HIS SECOND TARGET.
IT IS NOW ALBERT AND RICK.
ONE TARGET LEFT.
RICK COULD WIN IT, IMMUNITY AND
MASSAGE, WITH THIS TOSS.
NO!
CAN ALBERT DO IT?
ALKNOCKS HIS THIRD TEARING DOWN.
ALBERT WINS IMMUNITY AND
MASSAGE.
GOOD JOB, AL.
Jeff: ALBERT, COME ON OVER
( APPLAUSE )
NICE JOB.
ALBERT IS SAFE AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL, CANNOT BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE GOING TO GO
BACK TO CAMP, GET A BUSH SHOWER
FULL OF FRESH WATER.
YOU WILL THEN LIE DOWN ON A
MASSAGE TABLE, GET A
PROFESSIONAL MASSEUSE, NICE,
NATURAL OILS, WORK OUT THOSE
CINCHES.
RIGHT NEXT TO YOUR MASSAGE TABLE
IS A SECOND TABLE.
CHOOSE ONE MORE PERSON TO JOIN
YOU FOR A MASSAGE.
BIG DECISIONS YOU'RE MAKING IN A
VERY COMPLICATED SOCIAL GAME
RIGHT NOW.
WHAT MAKES IT SO TOUGH
BECAUSE EACH PERSON OVER HERE IS
A FAMILY MEMBER OF MINE.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE COACH
ON THIS.
Jeff: COACH, COME ON OVER
( APPLAUSE ).
I GOTTA ASK ONE THING,
THOUGH, JEFF.
IS THERE ANY WAY I CAN PICK ONE
MORE?
Jeff: NO.
NO WAY?
CAN I GIVE MY REWARD AWAY,
THEN.
Jeff: YOU WANT TO GIVE YOUR
MASSAGE UP.
YEAH.
Jeff: TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
I WOULDN'T MIND DOING THAT.
SOMEBODY GIVE ME THEIR FOOD
REWARD NEXT TIME.
Jeff: IF YOU WANT TO GIVE
UP YOUR REWARD TO SOMEBODY ELSE
IN THIS GAME.
ABSOLUTE, IT IS YOUR REWARD.
I NEED THE FOOD, SO SOMEBODY
NEXT TIME, PLEASE.
THERE'S A GUY HERE WHO HAS A
BIRTHDAY IN TWO DAYS.
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT TO THE
BIRTHDAY BOY.
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT TO COCHRAN.
Jeff: COME ON OVER.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: SO, COCHRAN, IS A
MASSAGE SOMETHING YOU'RE LOOKING
FORWARD TO.
YEAH, I'VE GIVEN MY MOM
MACANNELS OVER THE YEARS BUT
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY PERSONALLY
RECEIVED ONE.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO BEING ON
THE RECEIVING END.
MY BROTHER IS IN TWO DAYS AND
THIS IS A GREAT GIFT.
I REALLY, REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
Jeff: ALBERT HAS IMMUNITY
SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
HE GIVES UP HIS REWARD.
COACH AND COCHRAN WILL GO BACK
ENJOY A NICE SHOWER AND A
MASSAGE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD BACK TO
CAMP. CONGRATS.
ALBERT OFFERED THE REWARD TO
ME.
THERE ARE ONLY TWO POSSIBLE
EXPLANATIONS FOR HIS DECISION.
ONE, HE WANTS TO WORK
STRATEGICALLY WITH ME AND IS
TRYING TO CURRIE FAVOR WITH ME
WHICH WOULD BE A GOOD OPTION.
TWO, IT WOULD BE A SWEET
FAREWELL GIFT FOR ME TO LIKE HIM
WHEN I GET ON THE JURY.
EITHER WAY. I HOPE I GET TO STAY
ONE MORE NIGHT IN THE SOUTH
PACIFIC.
THANK YOU, ALBERT.
OH, MY GOSH!
WALKING BACK INTO CAMP,
EVERYTHING IS LAID OUT FOR
COCHRAN AND I.
WE'VE GOT TWO MASSAGE TABLES
READY.
WE'VE GOT A SHOWER TO THE LEFT
SIDE.
WE'VE GOT TWO BEAUTIFUL SOUTH
PACIFIC WOMEN THAT ARE READY TO
MASSAGE US.
THERE'S OILS THERE.
EVERYTHING SMELLS BEAUTIFUL,
FRESH, NEW, CLEAN.
THE WATER'S LIKE-- IT LIKE
SMELLS SCENTED LIKE JASMINE OR
SOMETHING.
COCHRAN, IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
LET ME TELL YOU.
I'M TRYING NOT TO USE ALL THE
WATER.
YEAH, TRY A LITTLE BIT
HARDER.
UP TO THIS POINT, I'VE NEVER HAD
A MASSAGE.
I'M THRILLED TO SEE THAT, YOU
KNOW, SOME STUPID LITTLE WHITE
LIE ABOUT WHEN MY BIRTHDAY WAS--
WHICH ACTUALLY TOOK PLACE SIX
MONTHS AGO-- IS HELPING ME
SOMEWHAT IN THIS GAME, EVEN IF
IT'S TO GET A FREE MASSAGE.
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
IT FEELS GREAT.
I MEAN, HAVING A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
STROKE THE INSIDE OF MY LEGS IS
A NEW EXPERIENCE FOR ME.
THIS IS JUST AMAZINGLY
REJUVENATING TO HAVE THIS KIND
OF TREATMENT OUT HERE ON DAY 30.
I COULDN'T ASK FOR ANYTHING
BETTER THAN THAT.
ACTUALLY, I COULD ASK FOR
COCHRAN'S LIFE TO BE SAVED
TONIGHT.
I WILL FIGHT FOR MY MAN COCHRAN
WITH MY LAST DYING BREATH.
OF THAT YOU CAN BE ASSURED, MY
YOUNG WARRIOR.
I'VE UPGRADED TO WARRIOR.
WASN'T I A STUDENT BEFORE?
YOU'RE A YOUNG WARRIOR RIGHT
NOW.
AFTER I RECEIVED MY SPA
REWARD, I PULLED ASIDE ALBERT,
NOT ONLY TO THANK HIM BUT TO
KIND OF GET A FEELING OF WHETHER
HE WAS WILLING TO CONTINUE
WORKING WITH ME, KNOWING FULL
WELL THAT MY NAME IS, YOU KNOW,
THE ONE BEING FLOATED AROUND THE
MOST TO BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
QUITE FRANKLY, IT'S NOT
LOOKING TOO GOOD FOR YOUR CASE.
I WAS PRETTY SURE COACH WAS ON
BOARD.
I WAS ABLE TO SWAY HIM A LITTLE
BIT AND TALK HIM INTO IT.
THE PROBLEM IS I DON'T THINK
HE'S READY TO MAKE A HUGE MOVE
THAT WOULD BE GETTING RID OF,
LIKE, A RICK--
I KNOW HE IS.
I KNOW FOR A FACT HE IS.
YOU THINK SO?
NO QUESTION.
COACH WILL VOTE OUT RICK.
HE CALLS HIM PRINCESS ALBERT.
WHEN DID YOU HEAR THAT?
AROUND THE FIRE YESTERDAY.
LOOK, I'M TELLING YOU I'M NOT--
OBVIOUSLY, I'M IN SURVIVAL MODE
RIGHT NOW, BUT I'M TELLING YOU
100%.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW HAPPY IT
WOULD MAKE ME TO SEE YOU GO
FATHER THAN RICK IN THIS GAME.
IT COULD MAKE ME ECSTATIC.
RICK, TO BEGIN WITH, HE'S
ABOUT AS SMART AS A BOWLING
BALL, AND THEN I HEAR HE'S
CHIRPING IN THE BACKGROUND,
CALLING ME NAMES, DROPPING A
PRINCESS HERE AND THERE.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME, RICK?
I HAVE A MIND TO GET RID OF RICK
ON THIS VOTE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF HE'D DO IT.
I PROMISE YOU THIS-- IF HE DOES
IT, YOU CAN COUNT ON ME, 100%.
HE'S PISSED OFF AT RICK NOW
BECAUSE HE HEARD ABOUT THE
PRINCESS ALBERT.
THAT ANNOYS HIM A LOT.
GOOD.
HE WANTS TO VOTE OUT RICK.
DUDE.
I'M ON BOARD.
ALBERT CAUGHT WIND THAT RICK WAS
CALLING HIM PRINCESS ALBERT,
PRINCE ALBERT BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
DO ANYTHING AROUND CAMP.
COCHRAN AND I TRYING TO USE THAT
INFORMATION TO TRY TO GET COACH
TO COME WITH US TO VOTE RICK
OFF.
I FEEL LIKE IF WE DON'T USE YOU
TO OUR MAXIMUM BENEFIT, PART OF
THE REASON WE WON THAT LAST
GROUP CHALLENGE AND WERE 6-6
INTO THE MERGE IS BECAUSE OF
YOU.
I THINK THAT WE OWE YOU MORE OF
A, YOU KNOW, DEBT.
I LIKE YOU.
I LIKE COACH.
YEAH.
I LIKE YOU, TOO.
I TALKED TO ALBERT.
HE GAVE ME THIS WHOLE SPIEL IT'S
NOT LOOKING SO GOOD.
MY DECISION TONIGHT AND WHICH
WAY I GO IS GOING TO DETERMINE
THE REST OF THIS GAME.
THERE IS A TIDE THAT IS COMING.
I EITHER TAKE IT AND GO WITH A
NEW ALLIANCE, OR STAY WITH MY
FIRST FIVE.
AS WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE SAYS,
THERE'S A TIDE THAT COMES IN THE
LIVES OF MEN THAT WHEN TAKEN,
LEADS TO GREAT FORTUNE.
BUT WHEN OMIDST IT, ALL THE REST
OF THEIR LIVES ARE BOUND IN
SHADOWS AND MISERY.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT I MAKE
THE RIGHT DECISION.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE THEY TAKE
THE RIGHT TIDE SO THAT I CAN
RIDE THAT TIDE ALL THE WAY TO
THE END OF THIS GAME THAT I LOVE
SO DEARLY.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JIM.
KEITH.
DAWN.
AND WHITNEY.
COACH, WHERE DOES THIS RANK IN
TERMS OF ALL THE POSSIBILITIES
THAT COULD HAPPEN WITH TONIGHT'S
VOTE?
I THINK THE POSSIBILITIES ARE
ENDLESS.
I MEAN, THEY REALLY ARE BECAUSE
NOBODY REALLY KNOWS IF THEY'RE
GOING TO THE FINAL THREE, IF
THEY'RE FOUR, FIVE, SIX, OR
SEVEN.
THERE'S A NEW SCENARIO THAT'S
PRESENTED TO ME AND ALBERT AND
EVERYBODY HERE EVERY HOUR.
IT'S BEEN CRAZY.
Jeff: COCHRAN, DID YOU FEEL
THE SCRAMBLING HAPPENING TODAY?
OH, ABSOLUTELY BECAUSE I TOOK
PART IN IT.
I'M SURE IT'S GOING TO FILL THE
JURY WITH GLEE TO DISCOVER I'M
PROBABLY IN GREAT DANGER
TONIGHT, AND I FEEL LIKE AN
IDIOT KIND OF.
I DON'T MEAN TO SOUND GREEDY BUT
I'M HERE TO COLLECT A DEBT.
I GAVE LIFE TO THIS TRIED AND TO
BE TARGETED FOR SEVENTH IT'S A
LITTLE BIT HUMILIATING.
I FEEL A LITTLE BIT DUPED.
THE MASSAGE WAS ONE NICE WAY OF
PAYING OFF THE DEBT BUT I FEEL
LIKE I'M ENTITLED TO AT LEAST
ONE MORE NIGHT IN THIS GAME.
JUST TO COMMENT ON THAT POINT
I VOCALIZE TO THE TRIBE I
THOUGHT IT'S NOT IN THE BEST
INTEREST OF OUR QUOTE, UNQUOTE
IMAGE, TO USE AND ABUSE SOMEONE,
AND I DON'T REGRET MY DECISION
OF GIVING HIM THE REWARD, AND I
DON'T WANT HIM TO REGRET HIS
DECISION.
Jeff: COACH, DOES IT
CONCERN YOU A LITTLE WHEN YOU
HAVE ALBERT SAYING, "I THINK
COCHRAN'S RIGHT?"
AS EVERYBODY KNOWS, WE'RE IN
THIS GOOD STANDING BECAUSE
COCHRAN MADE A MOVE THAT SOME
PEOPLE CONSIDERED COWARDICE.
OTHERS, INCLUDING MYSELF,
THOUGHT IT WAS VERY BOLD AND
COURAGEOUS.
Jeff: RICK, ARE YOU WORRIED
AT ALL IF COCHRAN DOES PLAY HIS
CARD TONIGHT THAT MEANS IT'S ONE
OF THE OTHER SIX?
OH, ABSOLUTELY BECAUSE IT'S A
MILLION BUCKS, YEAH.
I'VE GOT MY BAGS PACKED.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO GO, BUT,
YEAH.
Jeff: EDNA, ARE YOU
EMOTIONAL TONIGHT OR ARE YOU--
YEAH, I'M A LITTLE EMOTIONAL
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE I'M SIXTH,
YOU KNOW, THE PERCEPTION THAT
THE SIX WERE EQUAL.
THAT WAS A DELUSION.
I WAS LED TO THINK THAT I WAS
EQUAL IN CERTAIN PEOPLE'S MINDS,
WE WEREN'T.
Jeff: SO YOUR EMOTION IS
ANGER, HURT, SADNESS?
SADNESS.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE ALREADY BEEN
DECEIVED LEADING UP TO HERE,
LIKE, OKAY, I'M SIXTH.
THAT DOESN'T FEEL VERY GOOD.
Jeff: SO, EDNA, IF COCHRAN
BELIEVES HE'S SEVENTH AND YOU
BELIEVE YOU'RE SIXTH, ALL YOU
NEED IS TO FIND WHO'S FIFTH AND
WHO'S FOURTH BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT
IN THE MONEY, EITHER.
YEAH, SURE.
TALK TO PEOPLE AND FIND A LITTLE
CRACK, AND EXPANDING THAT.
IT'S A LITTLE BIT OF A PUBLICITY
ACT.
SO WE HAVE TO FIND CERTAIN
ANGLES AND APPROACH THEM.
Jeff: JEFF.
Jeff: BRANDON.
EVERYBODY HERE KNOWS WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN FOR THESE TWO.
THAT'S WHY TONIGHT I'M VOTING
OUT COCHRAN AND THEN THE NEXT
NIGHT MY VOTE IS FOR EDNA.
LET'S NOT TRY TO BE SO GRAY OUT
THERE AND JUST GET IT OUT THERE.
I DO BELIEVE THERE'S BLACK AND
WHITE AND IF THERE'S GRAY, YOU
MIGHT AS WELL BE LYING, TO BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
Jeff: COACH, BRANDON NOW
POSES A HUGE PROBLEM FOR ANYBODY
IN HIS ALLIANCE.
HE IS NOT MALLEABLE.
SO IF SOMETHING GOES HAYWIRE
WITH OUR PLAN, BRANDON AIN'T
GOING TO HELP.
RIGHT, THE FACT THAT BRANDON
IS NOT MALLEABLE IN THIS GAME IS
BOTH A BLESSING AND A CURSE.
IF YOU'RE WITH HIM, YOU KNOW
THAT HE'S NOT GOING TO TURN ON
YOU, BUT YOU'RE ALSO AFRAID THAT
HE'S GOING TO SPILT APPLE CART.
Jeff: BRANDON, ARE YOU
EXHAUSTED RIGHT NOW?
YEAH.
Jeff: WHAT HAS TRIED YOU
THE MOST IN THIS GAME?
I WANT TO DO WRONG THINGS.
I'M HUMAN.
BUT I-- THERE'S SOMETHING ST
STRONGER INSIDE ME THAT WON'T
LET ME.
ANYTHING WORTH HAVING IS NOT
GOING TO BE EASY.
SO THAT'S ALL I'M TELLING MYSELF
IN MY HEAD.
ANYTHING WORTH HAVING IS NOT
GOING TO BE EASY.
THAT'S ALL.
Jeff: COCHRAN, AS HARD AS
IT IS TO SEE BRANDON UPSET FROM
A GAME POINT OF VIEW, IT'S A
SPARK OF LIFE.
MAYBE THIS IS TOO MUCH FOR HIM.
I MEAN, I THINK BRANDON'S
REVEALED HE'S PROBABLY NOT THE
BEST PERSON TO BE IN A STRATEGIC
PARTNERSHIP WITH.
TALKING STRAIT WITH BRANDON IS
LIKE TALKING TO YOU ABOUT SHIRTS
THAT AREN'T BLUE BLUE.
HE DOESN'T COMPREHEND IT.
IT ISN'T IN HIS VOCABULARY.
I WOULDN'T WANT TO COME UP WITH
STRATEGIC IDEAS WITH HIM BECAUSE
HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THAT
LANGUAGE.
Jeff: ALBERT, IS THAT TRUE
ABOUT BRANDON?
CHARACTER ASIDE, NOT THE
GREATEST STRATEGY PLAYER OUT
HERE?
YEAH.
I THINK IT'S SOMETIMES UNSETTLE
GLG SO IF SOMETHING HAPPENS IN
THIS GAME AND YOUR ALLIANCE HAS
TO MAKE A DIFFERENT MOVE AND
BRANDON SAYS, "WISH I COULD,
CAN'T."
I THINK RIGHT NOW THE WAY OUR
TRIBE IS I'M NOT CONCERNED ABOUT
ANYTHING HAPPENING IN THE GAME.
AND I THINK--
IF EDNA WINS IMMUNITY, WHAT
HAPPENS?
Jeff: WOW.
THEN IT STARTS.
Jeff: THIS HAS BEEN A BIT
OF AN EYE-OPENING TRIBAL, HASN'T
IT?
NO?
NO.
Jeff: REALLY?
SO, COCHRAN, HOW FRUSTRATING IS
IT IF THE MOVE YOU MADE WAS FOR
NAUGHT?
IT'S INTENSELY FRUSTRATING.
I THOUGHT I WAS BEING SOME SAVVY
GAME PLAYER AND THEN I GET VOTED
OUT IN A WORSE POSITION THAN I
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE IF I STUCK
WITH MY OLD TRIBE.
IT'S EXTREMELY HUMILIATING.
I PRIDE MYSELF ON BEING A
"SURVIVOR" EXPERT.
I HOPE THIS TURNS OUT TO BE ONE
OF THE MOST IDIOTIC MOVES IN THE
HISTORY OF THE GAME.
Jeff: IT HAS BEEN ONE OF
THE MOST INTERESTING AND
REVEALING TRIBAL COUNCILS OF THE
SEASON.
ALBERT HAS THE NECKLACE, CANNOT
VOTE FOR ALBERT.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
BRANDON, YOU'RE UP.
COCHRAN, THANKS FOR MAKING
THE BIG MOVE WHEN YOU MADE IT.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
RICK, I'M WRITING YOUR NAME
DOWN.
HOPEFULLY THE OTHER THREE PEOPLE
IN OUR SUBALLIANCE WILL BE
WRITING YOUR NAME DOWN, TOO
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, COCHRAN.
RICK.
TWO VOTES RICK, ONE VOTE
COCHRAN.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES COCHRAN,
TWO VOTES RICK.
COCHRAN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES COCHRAN, TWO
VOTES RICK.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC,"
COCHRAN.
THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
COCHRAN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
JEFF PROBST, JUST SNUFFED MY
TORCH.
IT'S UNREAL.
A DREAM COME TRUE.
SEE YOU, COCHRAN.
GEEZ.
Jeff: JUST TAKE THE STEPS.
YEAH.
Jeff: WELL, THERE WAS A LOT
OF INFORMATION REVEALED TONIGHT,
AND YOUR FUTURE IN THIS GAME
WILL BE DETERMINED BY WHAT YOU
DO WITH IT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
OUR TRIBE IS HONOR AND
INTEGRITY, AND THEN YOU ALLOW
SUCH BEHAVIOR.
Jeff: BRANDON'S IN DEEP
TROUBLE.
ON A DAY WE THOUGHT EDNA WAS
DEFINITELY GOING TO GO HOME
THAT'S NOT THE CASE ANYMORE.
Jeff: AND COCHRAN IS IN
EVEN DEEPER.
YOU HAVE A CHANCE.
HE REALLY DOESN'T STAND A
CHANCE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
COCHRAN, COCHRAN, COCHRAN.
THE BICK MOVE I MADE AT THE
MERGE IN JUMPING OVER TO UPOLU,
IN RETROSPECT, MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
THE BEST MOVE.
I ABSOLUTELY FEEL LIKE UPOLU
USED ME.
THE FACT THAT THEY DID
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO SHOW ANY
SORT OF GRATITUDE, APART FROM