Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AT THE UPOLU
TRIBE--
THERE WAS FIVE OF US SIT, OUT
BY THE CANOE.
Jeff: A RANDOM CONVERSATION
ON THE FIRST NIGHT TURNED INTO
A
FINAL FIVE PACT.
LATER, COACH ADDED EDNA TO THE
GROUP AS THE SIXTH.
IT'S MY JOB TO PROTECT HER.
Jeff: AFTER THE MERGE, WHEN
THE ALLIANCE OF SIX WAS IN
DANGER--
THERE'S A LINE IN THE SAND.
COME ACROSS THAT LINE.
Jeff: COACH PERSUADED
COCHRAN TO FLIP AND JOIN HIS
ALLIANCE AS THEIR SEVENTH.
I GOT COCHRAN ON OUR SIDE TO
PLAY THE REST OF THE THIS GAME.
I CONVINCED HIM HE WILL BE
VALUED AND LOVED OVER HERE.
Jeff: BUT ON DAY 29 WHEN HE
WAS ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK, COCK
RAN USED ALL THE TRICKS HE
LEARNED AT HARVARD LAW TO MAKE
A
FINAL SUMMATION.
HE SAID I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
FEEL INDEBTEDDED TO ME.
DON'T
FEEL INDEBTEDDED TO YOU.
SCREW YOU.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
ONCE AGAIN BRANDON PUT HIS
FOOT IN HIS MOUTH.
EVERYBODY HERE KNOWS WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN WITH THESE TWO.
TONIGHT I VOTE OUT COCHRAN, AND
THE NEXT NIGHT I VOTE FOR EDNA.
Jeff: COCHRAN HEADS TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND AND EDNA HAS
TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO STAY IN
THE GAME.
OH, COCHRAN.
COCHRAN, HAS ARRIVED.
COCHRAN, COCHRAN, COCHRAN.
WHY?
DIDN'T YOU LEARN YOUR LESSON?
I GOT-- YOU KNOW, I GOT
SCREWED.
I'M HUMILIATED.
OH, GOD.
I'M SORRY, BUDDY.
IT HAPPENS TO THE BEST OF US.
THE BIG MOVE I MADE AT THE
MERGE IN JUMPING OVER TO UPOLU,
IN RETROSPECT, MAY NOT HAVING
HAVE BEEN THE BEST MOVE.
I ABSOLUTELY FEEL LIKE UPOLU
USED ME.
THE FACT THAT THEY DID
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO SHOW
REQUEST SORT OF GRATITUDE,
APART
FROM LIP SERVICE, IS INSULTING
TO ME.
DRANK THE KOOL-AID.
I KNOW YOU DID.
WELL, I'VE GOT A WAY THAT YOU
CAN NOT LET THEM WIN.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS VOTE FOR
ME IF I MAKE IT.
IF YOU HAD A CHOICE BETWEEN ME
OR COACH?
UHM... I'M NOT READY TO
COMMIT TO THAT.
AND IT'S KIND OF INSULTING
THAT'S THAT IT'S ALREADY A
FORGONE CONCLUSION IN HIS MIND
THAT I'M GOING TO LOSE AT THE
DUEL.
WHAT IF I DEMOLISH YOU IN A
HOW COME THAT'S NEVER TALKED
ABOUT?
THAT'S TRUE.
AS A POSSIBILITY.
AND IF YOU MAKE IT TO THE END
I'LL VOTE FOR YOU?
REALLY?
HOW ABOUT THAT?
DO I HAVE A CHANCE OF BEATING
YOU AT A DUEL?
YOU HAVE A CHANCE.
EVERYONE HAS A CHANCE.
HE REALLY DOESN'T STAND A
CHANCE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
GOOD MORNING.
ALBERT, WHENEVER YOU'RE
READY, BRO, I'D LIKE TO SAY
MORNING PRAY BEFORE EVERYBODY
DISBURSES.
SHE SAID SHE'S NOT PART OF
THIS TRIBE.
SO SHE WALKED OFF.
WHEN BRANDON ANNOUNCED HE
WANTED TO PRAY WITH THE TRIBE,
HE MADE IT CLEAR TO ME
YESTERDAY
AT TRIBAL THAT I'M NOT PART OF
THE TRIBE.
I'M NEXT TO GO.
YOU SLEEP NEXT TO THESE PEOPLE
AND THEY TELL YOU FROM DAY ONE
THAT YOU'RE INCLUDED IN THE
TRIBE, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH,.
AND WE'RE GOING TO PREACH
HONESTY AND INTEGRITY.
I FEEL LIKE COCHRAN HAS.
I FEEL DUPED.
THANK YOU FOR EDNA, FATHER
GOD.
COACH AND HOW CAN YOU BE NOT
THE LEADER?
HE'S THE ONE PREACHING IT DAY
IN
AND DAY OUT.
THIS IS REALITY.
THIS IS REAL LIFE FOR THESE
INDIVIDUALS, AND TO TREAT ME
LIKE A SECOND-CLASS CITIZEN, IS
THAT TRUE LIFE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE I VOLUNTEERED
TO
COME OUT HERE TO BE DECEIVED BY
EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY GETS DECEIVED.
IT'S JUST EYE JUST FEEL LIKE
THE DECEPTION WAS THAT WE WERE
SIX STRONG, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
BUT WE WERE.
NOW THERE'S SIX, OKAY.
OKAY, IF YOU WANT--
CAN I JUST FINISH--
SORRY, SORRY.
WE ARE A TRIBE.
IT NOW GOINGS AN INDIVIDUAL
GAME.
YOU GUYS ARE TELLING ME IT'S
AN INDIVIDUAL GAME AT FIVE.
DO YOU SEE?
EDNA, PLEASE JUST--
AND, CLEARLY YOU KNEW AND
EVERYBODY ELSE KNEW THAT I WAS
A
SECOND-CLASS CITIZEN IN THIS
AND
THAT'S WHAT I DON'T LIKE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU RIGHT NOW
EVERYBODY!
I JUST FEEL LIKE ONE GUY--
WE HAVE TREE MAIL!
YES, WE DO!
A 19-YEAR-OLD HIGH SCHOOL
DROPOUT.
I'M HERE, EVERYONE.
WHO'S ADVERTISED THAT HE'S
CRAZY TO DICTATE TO ME THE
DIRECTION OF MY OWN DESTINY
HERE.
TREE MAIL!
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF EDNAS
MELTED DOWN, BRANDON COMES
RUNNING INTO CAMP, "GUYS GUYS,
GUYS, IT'S "IT'S A SPRINT TREE
MAIL.
YOU'RE ALL TOGETHER NOW SO
THE BEST JUST GOT BETTER.
BEFORE THE DUEL CHEER AS YOU
WATCH YOUR VIDEO LETTERS.
AWESOME.
VIDEOS FROM HOME.
I WANT TO CRY RIGHT NOW, MAN.
HEY, RICKY.
I'M HERE.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
HOLY COW.
THE KIDS, OF COURSE, ARE
MISSING YOU.
THE DOGS THOUGHT YOU FELL OFF
THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
AND I'M SURE SICK OF FEEDING
THOSE COWS.
HURRY HOME.
WE MISS YOU LOTS AND LOVE YOU
LOTS, LOVE YOU.
HEY, EDNA, IT'S ME.
I'M SURE YOU'RE DOING REALLY
WELL OUT THERE BUT WE WORRY
ABOUT YOU A LOT AND I HOPE THAT
IT'S BECOME EVERYTHING THAT YOU
WANTED IT TO BE.
IT WAS VERY EMOTIONAL TO SEE
MY SISTER BECAUSE SHE'S A SMALL
VERSION OF ME-- AN
OVER-ACHIEVER.
I'M VERY PROUD OF HER.
I DON'T TELL HER ENOUGH.
HI, SOPHIE.
I WASN'T SURE YOU WERE GOING TO
GET THIS FAR IN THE GAME, BUT
DID YOU.
YOU PROMISED YOU WOULD, AND YOU
DELIVERED, SOPHIE.
LOVE YOU VERY MUCH.
BYE.
HI, ALBERT.
IT'S ME.
HERE ISLAND.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW NO
MATTER WHAT HAPPENS YOU'RE A
WINNER TO ME, AND MAY GOD BLESS
YOU, SON, I LOVE YOU.
COACH, WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
MY BROTHER.
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU FROM THE
BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
I'M EXTREMELY PROUD OF YOU.
MOM AND DAD ARE PROUD OF YOU,
AND YOU'RE THE MAN.
KEEP IT GOING, BROTHER.
HEY, BRANDON, I'M HERE ON THE
ISLAND, AND--
THAT'S YOUR DAD?
AND I'VE HAD A LONG TIME TO
KIND OF THINK ABOUT HOW MUCH I
REALLY LOVE AND YOU MISS YOU
AND
NO ONE WILL EVER BE ABLE TO
TAKE
YOUR PLACE.
AND I JUST WANT YOU TO MAKE
GOOD
DECISION, NOT BASED OFF OF THE
GAME SO MUCH.
MAKE DECISIONS BASED OFF OF
YOUR
HEART.
DO WHAT YOUR HEART TELLS YOU.
YES, SIR.
AND YOU WON'T GO WRONG.
LOVE YOU, MAN.
TO SEE MY FATHER WAS AMAZING
TODAY.
I LOVE HIM, MAN, AND I CAN'T
WAIT TO JUST SEE HIM, WHETHER I
GET TO SPEND TIME WITH HIM OR
NOT.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
OZZY WILL BE BATTLING AGAINST
COCHRAN.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
BEFORE WE GET TO YOUR DUEL,
THIS
MORNING IN TREE MAIL YOU GUYS
RECEIVED THE EVO 3-D FROM
SPRINT.
EDNA, I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
NOW, OZZY, COCHRAN, THERE IS A
TWIST TO TODAY'S DUEL, BUT I'LL
SAVE THAT FOR A MOMENT AND GET
TO WHAT IS MORE PRESSING FOR
THE
TWO OF YOU, WHICH IS WHAT COULD
BE A MILLION-DOLLAR DUEL.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU WILL USE
GRABBLING THOOKS RETRIEVE THREE
BAGS.
EACH BAG CONTAINS A BALL.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THREE BAGS,
YOU WILL USE ONE BALL TO SOLVE
THE TABLE MAZE.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
STAYS ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
THE LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD.
THEIR ADVENTURE OVER, NO SHOT
AT
THE MONEY.
BIG STAKES.
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
COCHRAN'S FIRST TOSS A LITTLE
SHORT.
OZZY'S FIRST TOSS LANDS HIS
FIRST BAG.
ON THE END, COCHRAN, ON THE
END OF THE ROPE.
Jeff: COCHRAN GETTING SOME
HELP FROM HIS FORMER
TRIBEMATES.
OZZY WITH HIS SECOND TOSS AND
ANOTHER BAG.
COCHRAN, CAN HE SLIDE IT OVER?
THERE YOU GO, THERE YOU GO.
Jeff: COCHRAN HAS HIS FIRST
BAG, GOTTA GET IT BAG.
OZZY HAS TWO BAGS.
ONE BAG LEFT.
THAT SHOULD DO IT TO GRAB HIS
THIRD AND FINAL BAG.
OZZY HAS HIS THREE BAGS.
TAKE THEM BACK TO THE PLATFORM.
ENVISION IT, COCHRAN.
WATCH THAT ROPE FLYING OUT
THERE
AND SNAGGING THAT BAG.
KEEP FIGHTING, COCHRAN.
LET'S GO.
OZZY WORKING ON THE TABLE MAZE.
COCHRAN WITH ANOTHER GREAT
TOSS.
HE'S GOT HIS SECOND BAG.
LET'S GO, PICK IT UP!
GET THAT THING BACK!
OZZY DOING A NICE JOB ON THAT
MAZE, TAKING HIS TIME.
KNOWS HE'S GOT A BIG LEAD RIGHT
NOW.
COCHRAN WITH A GREAT TOSS.
THAT WILL GET HIS THIRD BAG.
GO, HERCULES.
Jeff: GET IT BACK.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: COCHRAN NOW HAS HIS
BAG.
JUST NEED ONE BALL TO START
WORKING ON THAT MAZE.
OZZY VERY CALM ON THE MAZE GET,
CLOSER TO THE INNER CIRCLE.
SMOOTH AND EASY.
Jeff: COCHRAN GOING TO HAVE
TO GO FOR BROKE AND HE DOES.
COCHRAN QUICKLY IN THE MIDDLE
OF
THIS MAZE.
COCHRAN MADE UP A LOT OF TIME
WITH ONE VERY AGGRESSIVE MOVE.
OZZY, HE'S CLOSE, BUT IT'S VERY
DIFFICULT.
OZZY FALLS OUT, OZZY HAS TO
START OVER.
COME ON, BUDDY.
Jeff: SUDDENLY, COCHRAN IS
BACK IN THIS DUEL.
TAKE YOUR TIME, HE'S NOWHERE
NEAR YOU.
Jeff: OZZY'S BALL DROPS
AGAIN.
COCHRAN IN LINE TO DEFEAT ONE
OF
HIS BIGGEST IDOLS IN THIS GAME.
COCHRAN-- OH, SO CLOSE.
COCHRAN DOPS OUT.
HE'S BACK TO THE START.
OZZY NOW HAS THE LEAD.
THIS DUEL IS STILL UP FOR
GRABS.
TAKE YOUR TIME, BUD.
GET BACK TO IT, GET BACK TO IT.
Jeff: COCHRAN HAVING A LOT
OF SUCCESS.
IT'S A CRAZY, UNWIELDY
STRATEGY,
BUT IT'S WORKING.
TAKE YOUR TIME, BUDDY.
COCHRAN NEARING THAT INNER
CIRCLE.
OZZY NEARING THE INNER CIRCLE.
BOTH VERY CLOSE.
WE HAVE A DUEL GOING HERE.
COCHRAN WITH A NICE MOVE.
TAKE YOUR TIME,
COCHRAN, STAY COOL.
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO STAY CALM
WITH THIS MAZE.
OZZY WITH A GOOD SAVE.
IT IS OZZY AND COCHRAN.
RIGHT NOW EITHER GUY COULD WIN
IT.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
Jeff: BOTH GUYS WITHIN
INCHES OF THE FINISH.
COCHRAN VERY CLOSE AND HE DROPS
OUT IN THE INNER CIRCLE AGAIN.
OZZY WINS THE DUEL AND STAYS
ALIVE!
( APPLAUSE )
IT'S OKAY.
OH, MAN, COCHRAN!
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
GOOD JOB, COCHRAN.
GOOD JOB, OZZY.
DUDE, YOU ALMOST GOT ME!
Jeff: COCHRAN.
YEAH.
Jeff: YOU ALMOST DID IT.
EVEN THOUGH I DIDN'T WIN--
I-- I WAS GOING UP PROBABLY ONE
OF THE MOST CHALLENGE
DOMINATORS
TO EVER PLAY THIS GAME AND TO
COME SO CLOSE IS DREAM FULL
FILMMENT FOR ME.
I LOVE "SURVIVOR."
I LOVE, I BREATHE "SURVIVOR."
TO BE HERE.
TO BE FACING YOU.
TO HEAR YOU SAY, "COME ON IN,
GUYS," BEFORE THE CHALLENGE.
I'M THINKING, I'M ONE OF THE
GUYS!
HE'S TALKING ABOUT ME.
IT'S ONE SURREAL MOMENT AFTER
ANOTHER AND I'M TALKING TO KIND
OF PREVENT MYSELF FROM GETTING
TEARY EYED AND STUFF BECAUSE
THIS HAS BEEN, BY FAR, THE MOST
INCREDIBLE MOMENT OF MY LIFE.
Jeff: REALLY?
YEAH.
Jeff: WHAT ARE THE TEARS --
WHERE ARE THEY COMING FROM?
IT'S COMING FROM A
REALIZATION THAT I'M NOT THE
PERSON I NECESSARILY THOUGHT I
WAS.
AND THAT I CAN BE A BETTER
PERSON THAT'S MORE PLEASED WITH
HIMSELF AND THE DECISIONS THAT
HE MAKES AND THE THINGS HE
PURSUES.
Jeff: I GOTTA TELL YOU,
COCHRAN, BECAUSE YOU RISKED,
BECAUSE YOU WEREN'T THE MOST
LIKELY GUY ON THIS SHOW AND YOU
FOUND YOUR WAY OUT HERE AND YOU
WERE RIDICULED AND PEOPLE
PICKED
ON YOU AND YOU DIDN'T BACK
DOWN.
IN FACT YOU DID ONE OF THE
BIGGEST MOVES IN THIS GAME.
I THINK A PART OF YOU DIED OUT
HERE AND A NEW PART REBORN.
THANK YOU
( APPLAUSE ).
Jeff: AND NOW,
UNFORTUNATELY, THE ADVENTURE
HAS
COME TO AN END.
IT IS TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
( APPLAUSE ).
GOOD JOB, MAN.
GOOD JOB, BRO.
THANK YOU.
MAKE THAT SWEATER VEST
( APPLAUSE )
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, OZZY, YOU
STAY ALIVE IN THIS GAME.
YOU ARE ONE STEP CLOSER TO
GETTING BACK INTO THE GAME.
IN A MOMENT, YOU'RE GOING TO
MAKE A VERY BIG DECISION THAT
IMPACTS THE SIX OF THESE GUYS,
BUT BEFORE YOU MAKE THAT
DECISION, I WANT YOU TO KNOW
WHAT IS AT STAKE.
SOPHIE, BEEN OUT HERE 31 DAYS.
THERE IS NOTHING LIKE THE LOVE
OF A DAD TO MAKE IT ALL GOOD.
Y THURSTON, COME ON OUT.
OH, MY GOD.
( APPLAUSE )
THURSTON!
I LOVE YOU.
Jeff: GIVE HIM A QUICK HUG,
SOPHIE.
COME ON BACK.
I WANT REESE EASE PEANUT
BUTTER CUPS, AND FRESH MADE
BANANA BREAD AND A HAMBURGER.
Jeff: EDNA, HERE'S YOUR
SISTER, DEBBIE.
( APPLAUSE )
OKAY, HOW ARE YOU?
I'M VERY WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
REALLY?
I'M OKAY.
Jeff: COACH, A LOT OF
PEOPLE ON THE FENCE ABOUT YOU.
IS HE FOR REAL?
WHO KNOWS?
MY BROTHER KNOWS.
Jeff: YOUR BROTHER, PETE,
WOULD KNOW.
PETE, COME ON DOWN.
GIVE COACH SOME LOVE.
MAN, YOU LOOK AWESOME.
Jeff: THAT'S A HUG.
SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
Jeff: RICK, COME ON DOWN,
BROTHER.
KATY, COME OUT HERE.
COME ON, DARRYLIN'.
COME OVER HERE.
Jeff: RICK NEEDS SOME
FAMILY LOVE.
I DON'T SMELL VERY GOOD BUT
YOU LOOK GOOD.
GET A ROOM.
Jeff: ALBERT, HERE'S YOUR
MOM, ANNIE.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
Jeff: BRANDON, YOUR DAD,
SEAN, RUSSELL HANS' BROTHER, IS
HERE TO GIVE YOU SOME LOVE.
COME ON OUT, SEAN.
( APPLAUSE )
Jeff: WOW.
THAT WAS A LOT OF EMOTION.
SO NOW, OZZY, YOU HAVE A BIG
DECISION TO MAKE.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO SPEND SOME
TIME WITH THEIR LOVED ONE.
A LOT OF STRATEGY IN WHO YOU
GIVE LOVE TO.
YOU COULD CURRY A LOT OF FAVOR
SHOULD YOU GET BACK IN THIS
GAME.
I CHOOSE ALBERT.
Jeff: ALBERT WILL GET TO
SPEND SOME TIME WITH HIS MOM.
I'M SORRY, GUYS, IT'S JUST --
DON'T BE SORRY YET.
CHOOSE ONE MORE PERSON, OZZY.
COACH.
Jeff: COACH, GOING TO GET
SOME LOVE FROM HIS BROTHER,
PETE.
CHOOSE ONE FINAL PERSON, OZZY.
OH!
BRANDON.
Jeff: BRANDON WILL GET TO
SPEND TIME WITH HIS DAD.
THAT MEANS RICK'S WIFE, KATY,
EDNA'S SISTER, DEBBIE, AND
SOPHIE'S DAD, THURSTON, YOUR
TIME OUT HERE IS DONE.
WAVE YOUR GOOD-BYES AND HEAD
OUT.
BYE, SWEETIE.
LOVE YOU.
Jeff: SOPHIE, RICK, EDNA,
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SORRY, GUYS.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO, COACH,
ALBERT, BRANDON, YOU HAVE THE
EVO 3D FROM SPRINT.
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT.
CAPTURE THESE MEMORIES.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE OF THE PHONE
BECAUSE ALL OF YOU GUYS ARE
GOING TO SPEND YOUR TIME ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
LEAD THE WAY, OZZY.
GET EVERYBODY AND TAKE THEM TO
YOUR HOME, SOMETHING YOU GUYS
HAVE NOT EXPERIENCED, SOMETHING
YOU GUYS WILL NOT FORGET.
YEAH, SO THIS IS IT.
DOES RAIN GET IN HERE?
A LITTLE BIT.
THIS IS A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY TO BE ON "SURVIVOR.
IT'S A ONCE-IN-A-10-MILLION
OPPORTUNITY TO GET TO THE LOVED
ONES' VISIT.
AND YOU YOUR MOM.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
THIS PHONE ROCKS, MAN.
FIRST OF ALL, ANY TYPE OF
TECHNOLOGY, YOU COULD BRING OUT
A PHONE FROM 1995 AND IT WOULD
MAYBE LOOK SOMEWHAT COOL OUT
HERE, AND HERE'S THIS FLAT
SCREEN PHONE.
THAT'S CRAZY!
CHECK IT OUT, MAN.
CHECK OUT THE 3D ACTION HERE.
LET ME SEE THIS.
OH, DUDE!
HOLY SMOKES.
SO THIS COULDN'T HAVE COME AT
A BETTER TIME.
THIS IS AN INCREDIBLE
PICK-ME-UP
AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME.
I THINK OZZY PICKED ME IN THE
HOPES I WOULD BE IN HIS CORNER.
I GOT ONE BETTER FOR YOU OZZY.
I'M IN YOUR HOUSE.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
I'M NOT GOING-- I'M NOT GOING
TO
B.S. YOU MAN, I'M ALWAYS GOING
TO BE STRAIGHT WITH YOU AND I
WANT YOU TO BE STRAIGHT WITH ME
AND I WANT YOU TO KEEP THIS
CONVERSATION CONFIDENTIAL.
OF COURSE.
AS SOON AS YOU GET BACK FROM
REDEMPTION, THERE WILL BE
EITHER
SIX OR FIVE, AND I HAVE A
PERFECT FINAL THREE SCENARIO.
YOU, ME, AND ONE OTHER PERSON.
I'M GIVING YOU MY WORD, DUDE,
AS
A CHRISTIAN MAN.
IF YOU'LL NOTICE IN THIS GAME,
I
SAY, HEY, IT WOULD BE GREAT TO
TAKE TOUT FINAL THREE.
WHEN I SAY AS A CHRISTIAN MAN I
PROMISE YOU THIS IS WHAT I WILL
DO THAT'S AN IRREVOCABLE
PROMISE.
I WANT TO TAKE HIM TO THE FINAL
THREE.
LET'S DO IT.
I CANNOT WAIT.
ME, TOO.
ALL RIGHT, COOL, MAN.
IT'S GOING TO BE SUCH AN
EXAMPLE TO PEOPLE.
IT'S GOING TO CHANGE PEOPLE'S
LIVES.
SPIT ON A MILLION DOLLARS.
SPIT ON THE SOLE "SURVIVOR."
WHAT ARE YOU HERE FOR, THEN?
I'M HERE TO SET AN EXAMPLE
FOR CHRIST, BRO.
AND I'M GOING TO PLAY THIS GAME
OUT WITH HONOR AND INTEGRITY
AND
LIKE CHRIST WOULD PLAY IT.
I KNOW YOU'RE LOYAL AND
THAT'S THE WAY I'VE ALWAYS
TAUGHT YOU TO BE.
BUT I'M JUST SAYING.
WHAT?
AT THE END OF THE DAY AND YOU
KNOW THAT A MOVE WOULD PUT YOU
INTO THE FINAL THREE--
NO.
BRANDON, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I'M NOT KIDDING YOU.
YOU CAME HERE TO WIN A
MILLION DOLLARS.
LET'S NOT LOSE PERSPECTIVE.
IT'S CHANGED.
IT'S CHANGED, MAN.
I'M SORRY IF IT MAKE US UPSET.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ME UPSET THAT
YOU WANT TO STAND ON THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE A CRIB BUT YOU'RE
ALSO HERE TO DO A JOB AND THAT
JOB IS TO BRING HOME THE GOLD.
I'M SEEING BRANDON FRAZZLED.
I'M SEEING HIM EYE DON'T LIKE
WHAT I SEE.
SO I'M REALLY GLAD THAT I CAME
TODAY BECAUSE IF I HAD TO GRADE
BRANDON ON THE WAY HE'S PLAYING
RIGHT NOW I'D PROBABLY GIVE HIM
ABOUT A "C."
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE HASN'T
GOTTEN VOTED OUT YET.
GOD ALSO WANTS US TO BE WISE,
BE
WISE AND MAKE A GOOD POSITION.
PUT YOUR FAMILY IN A GOOD
POSITION OR YOU CAN JUST GO
PREACH ON THE STREET CORNER AND
DON'T WORRY ABOUT MONEY.
JUST TRUST THAT GOD-- GOD--
DUDE,
OUR LIVES HAVE BEEN PLANNED OUT
SINCE WE WERE BORN, BRO.
HE HAS TO BEGIN TO PLAY THE
GAME AND PLAY IT TO WIN IT.
IT'S THE HANTZ WAY, BABY.
YOU HAVE GOT TO PUT YOURSELF
INTO THIS FINAL THREE, AND THEN
AT THAT POINT THAT'S WHEN IT'S
UP TO GOD.
I'M GLAD I CAME OUT HERE.
BECAUSE BRANDON REALLY LOOKS
LIKE HE'S NOT HOLDING TOGETHER
WELL.
YEAH.
SO I JUST WANTED TO CONFIRM
THAT YOU WERE GOING TO TAKE
HIM,
YOU KNOW, MAKE SURE-- WHERE YOU
REALLY WERE WITH HIM.
YEAH, YEAH, SURE.
YOU'RE THE SINGLE PERSON THAT
HE HAS ALL HIS EGGS IN BASKET.
AT THIS POINT, WHO DO YOU WANT
TO BRING TO THE FINAL THREE?
WHEN IT GET TO FIVE, I HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT--
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE A
DECISION.
I HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION--
BEFORE I LEAVE HERE, I'LL
TELL HIM WHATEVER YOU TELL HIM
TO DO, PERIOD.
IT'S IN YOUR HANDS.
SO THERE IT IS.
THAT'S IT.
BRANDON HANTZ'S DAD, A CHIP
OFF THE OLD BLOCK.
THEY'RE ALL CUT OF THE SAME
CLOTH.
BRANDON'S DAD COMES OUT HERE
AND
BASICALLY TRIES TO BULLY ME
INTO
MAKING SURE HIS SON GOES ALL
THE
WAY TO THE END AND WINS A
MILLION DOLLARS.
EVEN IF HE WINS A CHALLENGE,
HE GOES TO YOU TO ASK WHAT--
EVER SINGLE VOTE, I'LL GO TO
YOU TO ASK.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
ARE WE DOWN?
ARE WE STRAIGHT?
IT'S ALL ABOUT MANIPULATION
AND CONTROL AND THE HANTZ
FAMILY
ARE THE KINGPINS.
I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE ANYBODY
BROW BEAT ME AND HANDCUFF ME
INTO A FINAL THREE WITH
BRANDON.
THE KID IS A LOOSE CANNON.
( TICK-TICK-TICK )
HE IS A TICKING TIME BOMB.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, ALBERT,
I'LL
TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOUR
GOAL
IS TO KEEP MOVING ACROSS A
GIANT
PUZZLE BOARD.
YOU'LL TAKE TURNS FLIPPING OVER
A PUZZLE PIECE AND STEPPING ON
TO IT.
ONCE A PIECE IS TURNED OVER,
YOU
CAN NEVER STEP PACK ON TO IT.
ONCE YOU'RE OUT OF MOVES,
YOU'RE
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE AT TRIBAL CO
COUNCIL, ONE STEP CLOSER TO THE
MILLION DOLLARS.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
WHERE OZZY IS ANXIOUSLY
AWAITING
YOUR ARRIVAL.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, SOPHIE, YOU'RE UP
FIRST.
ALBERT.
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET AS BIG A
PIECE OF THIS PIE AS YOU CAN.
ONCE YOU RUN OUT OF YELLOW
TILES, YOU ARE OUT.
COACH, IS THIS CHALLENGE A
LITTLE BIT LIKE A METAPHOR FOR
THE GAME, THE MOVES YOU MAKE
EARLY WILL DICTATE YOUR SUCCESS
LATER?
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
GREAT METAPHOR, JEFF.
TOOK THE WORDS RIGHT OUT OF MY
MOUTH.
Jeff: SOPHIE.
ALBERT.
BRANDON WITH AN INTERESTING
MOVE, MOVES TOWARD ALBERT.
COACH IS MOVING CLOSER TO EDNA.
CIRCLE'S GETTING VERY SMALL.
LOOKS LIKE EDNA IS GETTING
SQUEEZED OUT.
EDNA JUST REDUCED BRANDON'S
OPTIONS QUITE A BIT.
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
Jeff: BRANDON FEELING VERY
CONFIDENT.
RICK MAKES HIS MOVE, AND WITH
THAT COACH GIVES WHAT APPEARS
TO
BE A DRAGON SLAYER MOVE.
IT LOOKED LIKE TO BE-- A LITTLE
DRAGON SLAYER.
ALBERT HAS ONE MOVE TO MAKE.
HE GOES INTO THE CENTER SQUARE,
AND THAT WILL BE ALBERT'S LAST
MOVE.
ALBERT IS OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
EDNA LOOKING AT HER LIMITED
OPTIONS.
BRANDON MAKES HIS LAST MOVE SER
MOANSLY.
BRANDON, OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE
( APPLAUSE ).
I'M KIND OF EXPLAINING
EXACTLY WHAT I DID OVER HERE.
Jeff: WHAT'S THAT?
I WAS TALKING TO HIM ABOUT MY
LITTLE VAULT GEE THERE.
Jeff: WHAT WAS IT?
I JUST WANTED TO COVER ENOUGH
SURFACE AREA TO WHERE A
PARTICULAR PERSON DIDN'T WIN
THIS IMMUNITY.
YOU CAN JUST USE MY NAME FROM
NOW ON LIKE YOU DO.
Jeff: EDNA, THEY TALKING
ABOUT YOU?
I DON'T THINK THEY WERE
TALKING ABOUT ANYBODY ELSE
HERE.
IT'S PRETTY STRAIGHTFORWARD.
I WAS SO UNLUCKY ENOUGH TO BE
NOT ON THE BEACH THE FIRST DAY,
AND NOW THAT REPERCUSSION, JUST
LIKE YOU USED THE ANALOGY, YOUR
MOVES ON DAY ONE, OR YOUR EARLY
MOVES HAVE IMPLICATIONS LATER
ON.
Jeff: EDNA, YOU'RE UP.
COACH.
COACH CAN FEEL THE NECKLACE.
HE HAS THE BIGGEST PIECE OF
REAL
ESTATE ON THE BOARD.
IT IS HIS CHALLENGE TO LOSE.
RICK.
RICK MAKES HIS LAST MOVE.
THANK YOU
( APPLAUSE ).
Jeff: TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
SOPHIE MAKES HER LAST MOVE.
SOPHIE'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE
( APPLAUSE )
EDNA, EDNA WITH EVERY MOVE YOU
MAKE, YOU SEEM TO GET MORE
AGITATED.
IT'S A BIT OF INSULT TO SAY
MILDLY.
IT'S BEEN A TEAM SPORT FOR SOME
INDIVIDUALS AND AT SOME POINT,
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
REALIZE
IT WILL BE AN INDIVIDUAL GAME.
Jeff: EDNA, MAKE YOUR LAST
MOVE.
WITH THAT, COACH WINS
INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
COACH, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE ).
THANK YOU, JEFF.
Jeff: COACH, SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT VOTE FOR COACH.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, EDNA,
RICK, BRANDON, SOPHIE, ALBERT,
AFTER 32 DAYS IN THE SOUTH
PACIFIC, SOMEBODY VOTED OUT
TONIGHT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
HELP A SISTER OUT, COACH.
BRANDON'S SO TRUTHFUL HE
STICKS HIS FREAKING SMELLY FOOT
IN HIS MOUTH AND GET IN
TROUBLE.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET THIS MAKE
ME DOWN.
IF SHE WANTS TO PUT ME AS HER
LITTLE BAD GUY TODAY, I'LL BE
THE BAD GUY.
HOPEFULLY MY TRIBE WILL STAY
STRONG AND AS LONG AS WE COI
HAVE MORE GAME TO PLAY AND I'M
GOING TO ENJOY THAT BREAKFAST
ON
DAY 39.
EVERY DAY, THE PEOPLE IN THIS
TRIBE SURPRISE ME WITH THE
THINGS THEY DO.
AND EVERY DAY I'M RECALCULATING
WHO I THINK THE JURY'S GOING TO
HATE WHO I THINK THE JURY'S
GOING TO LOVE.
AND BRANDON OPENED HIS MOUTH.
HE WAS REALLY RUDE TO EDNA.
THERE WAS NO REASON TO TELL HER
"WE'RE ALL TRYING TO GET YOU
OUT."
I MEAN, THAT'S A BULLYING THING
TO DO.
DO YOU BOYS NEED SOME WATER
FILTERED?
WHY DO YOU GOT TO DO THAT,
BRANDON?
AND I LIKE EDNA.
IT DIDN'T NEED TO HAPPEN.
SHE WAS CLEARLY NOT GOING TO
WIN
THE GAME SO WHY KICK HER IN THE
GUTS LIKE A LITTLE DOG, CALLING
A DOG OVER, COME HERE, COME
HERE, COME HERE, AND WHACK IT
IN
THE GUT WITH YOUR FOOT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
EDNA, I JUST WANTED TO LET
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE
YOU FEEL BAD OR ANYTHING.
WELL, YOU DID.
DID I REALLY?
YES, I WAS ABOUT TO CRY.
I FEEL LIKE I'M GOING TO CRY
NOW.
WELL, YOU KNOW ME IN ANY
SITUATION, I'M VERY TRANSPARENT
WITH WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
HOPEFULLY YOU RESPECT THAT.
I DIDN'T MEAN ANY HARM.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE RUDE WE
SAYING SOMEONE'S NAME.
THE FACT THAT YOU EVEN
BROUGHT IT UP IS A LITTLE BIT
UNNECESSARY TO MENTION.
I THINK.
ALL I CAN SAY IS I'M SORRY
AND I HOPE YOU ACCEPT MY
APOLOGY.
I MEAN, AT THIS POINT, IT'S
LIKE YOU ALREADY DID IT, SO.
I UNDERSTAND.
I ACCEPT THE CONSEQUENCES OF MY
ACTION.
BRANDON DID VERBALIZE AN
APOLOGY BUT IT'S INSIGNE TEAR.
IT'S LIKE BEATING YOUR WIFE.
AND THEN APPROXIMATIONING OR
BUYING HER A DIAMOND NECKLACE.
I BOUGHT HER A DIAMOND
NECKLACE.
I APOLOGIZED, AND THAT'S IT.
IN HIS MIND, IT'S LIKE OKAY,
SHE
APOLOGIZED.
LET'S MOVE ON TO THE NEXT
INSULT.
BRENDAN, I THINK, OFTEN
THINKS HIS APOLOGY ABSOLVES ALL
SIN.
MAYBE THAT'S TRUE IN CHURCH BUT
ON "SURVIVOR" PEOPLE ARE NOT AS
FORGIVING, YOU KNOW, AS JESUS
CHRIST IS.
AND EDNA IS NOT AS FORGIVING
AND
THE REST OF THE TRIBE-- IT
DIDN'T GO UNNOTICED WITH US.
I HAVE A PROPOSITION FOR YOU
ALL.
OBVIOUSLY, I WANT TO SAVE MY
OWN
HIDE AND LIVE ANOTHER DAY IN
THIS GAME.
MY CAMPAIGN RIGHT NOW IS AT THE
EXPENSE OF BRANDON.
WE'VE BEEN PREACHING THAT OUR
TRIBE IS ABOUT HONOR,
INTEGRITY,
AND PLAYING THIS LIKE IT'S REAL
LIFE.
AND I FEEL AS THO THE ACTIONS
OF
BRANDON IN THE LAST 32 DAYS
DON'T-- AREN'T REALLY
CONSISTENT
WITH THAT.
IT'S DAY 32, AND I ASK YOU TO
DEFINE WHAT HONOR AND INTEGRITY
IS.
DOES IT INCLUDE LYING TO YOUR
OTHER TRIBE MATES?
DOES IT INCLUDE ALL THESE
EMOTIONAL OUTBREAKS?
I JUST ASK YOU TO JUXTAPOSE
AGAINST THE WAY I PERFORMED IN
THIS GAME.
I JUST CANNOT ACCEPT THE FACT
THAT OUR TRIBE SAYS HONOR AND
INTEGRITY AND HONOR AND
INTEGRITY AND THEN YOU ALLOW
SUCH BEHAVIOR TO HAPPEN IN OUR
CAMP.
THAT IS ALMOST A HALL PASS FOR
HIM TO ACT IRRATIONALLY AROUND
CAMP AND EMOTIONALLY
DESTRUCTIVE
TO EVERYBODY AROUND US-- ME,
MIKAYLA, YOU GUYS, WHEN YOU
GUYS
WERE INVOLVED IN THE MIKAYLA
THING.
MY NECK IS IN THE GUILLOTINE
RIGHT NOW.
AND I'M JUST GIVING YOU GUYS--
PLEASE, GIVE ME ONE MORE DAY
HERE.
EDNA PROVOCATIVELY PUT
SOMETHING ON THE TABLE.
VOTE OUT BRANDON TONIGHT, KEEP
ME, AND THE FOUR OF US WILL
TAKE
OWNERSHIP OF THIS GAME.
SYSTEMATICALLY SHE JUST LAID IT
ALL THE OUT FOR US.
IF THERE'S ANY ARGUMENT FOR US
TO SEND SOMEBODY ELSE HOME
TONIGHT, SHE SERVED BRANDON UP
VO-PITCH STYLE.
A PITCH WE CAN KNOCK OUT OF THE
PARK.
ON A DAY WE DEFINITELY THOUGHT
EDNA WAS GOING TO GO HOME,
THAT'S NOT THE CASE ANYMORE.
ALL RIGHT, GIVE IT TO ME
STRAIGHT.
YOU TAKE AN INDEPENDENT JURY.
AND YOU PUT EDNA ON THE STAND
AND YOU PUT BRENDAN ON THE
STABBED.
WHO WILL BE CONVICTED GUILTY?
BRANDON.
WHO IS MORE DESERVING OF
STAYING?
IDNA.
ABSOLUTELY.
THEY DON'T WANT TO SEND BRANDON
TO REDEMPTION, HAVE HIM WIN AND
COME BACK.
THAT'S FINE AND GOOD AND
EVERYTHING.
IT'S JUST-- I HAVE TO ASK THIS
QUESTION BECAUSE IT'S
DEFINITELY
AN OPTION.
WOULD YOU BE-- I HAVE TO ASK IT
BECAUSE IT'S DEFINITELY AN
OPTION.
WILL YOU PLAY YOUR IDOL FOR ME?
NO.
WHAT ARE YOUR INTENTIONS FOR
THE IDOL.
WHEN DO YOU THINK YOU'LL USE
IT?
I DON'T THINK I'LL USE IT.
IF I USE THE IDOL RIGHT NOW,
EVERYBODY ELSE IN THE GAME NO
LONGER TRUST MEAS.
IF I PLAY THE IDOL, I'M FOR
SURE
THE NEXT PERSON TO GO.
IF I GIVE YOU THE IDOL THEY'RE
GOING TO VOTE MY ASS OFF.
LIKE, 100%.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GO DOWN
WITHOUT AT LEAST ATTEMPTING
EVERYTHING.
I ADMIRE THAT, I ADMIRE THAT.
YOU KNOW, ABSOLUTELY, YOU
SHOULD
GO UP AND TELL, YOU KNOW,
ALBERT
AND SOPHIE.
YOU SHOULD GO TELL ALBERT AND
SOPHIE I TALKED TO COACH AND
EVERYTHING IS COOL.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
SEE HOW THEY VOTE.
OBVIOUSLY I'M NOT GOING TO BE
WRITING MY NAME DOWN.
I'LL BE WRITING BRANDON'S NAME
DOWN.
ALL I NEED IS THE 22 OF YOU TOO
COME ON BOARD AND JUST-- I JUST
WANT TO HEAR IF THAT'S
SOMETHING
THAT YOU WOULD EVEN CONSIDER.
HONESTLY, I'M NOT GOING TO
B.S. YOU.
I'M GIVING IT LEGITIMATE
THOUGHT.
I JUST HAVE TO KNOW THAT OUR
NUMBERS ARE THERE.
RIGHT.
IT'S JUST YOU AND SOPHIE,
BASICALLY.
YOU'RE SAYING COACH IS 100%
IN RIGHT NOW.
ABSOLUTELY.
100%.
I PERSONALLY NEVER HEARD THAT
FROM HIM, BUT OKAY.
COACH IS 100%.
I'LL EAT-- THE ONLY THING I CAN
SAY IS I'LL EAT A PIECE OF HIS
( BLEEP ).
THAT'S HOW MUCH OF 100% I AM
THAT HE'S IN WITH THIS.
YOU KNOW, EDNA CAN KIND OF
FEEL THE HEAT BARING DOWN ON
HER.
BUT EDNA SMACKS REALLY GOOD
POINS.
EDNA SAID STRAIGHT UP, I'M NOT
A
THREAT.
I'M NOT GOING TO WIN THE GAME.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE VERY
COMPETITIVE IN CHALLENGES.
JUST SAVE MY NECK NOW AND I CAN
GUARANTEE YOU GUYS A PLACE IN
THE FINAL FOUR.
AT THIS POINT IN ANYTIME
SURVIVOR" ANY TIME YOU CAN HAVE
A PLACE THAT DEEP IN THE GAME,
IT'S APPEALING.
IF I CAN DO THAT, THERE'S A
CHANCE BRANDON MIGHT HAVE A BIG
SURPRISE TONIGHT.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JIM.
KEITH.
DAWN.
WHITNEY.
AND COCHRAN.
SO, EDNA, BASED ON TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, IT'S CLEAR YOU'RE IN
THE HOT SEAT TONIGHT.
WHEN YOU GO BACK TO CAMP, WHO
DO
YOU TARGET AS THE PERSON WHO
SHOULD GO HOME INSTEAD OF YOU?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO TARGET
BRANDON.
HIS OBJECTIONS, BEHAVIORS, AND
WORDS HAVE BEEN INCONSISTENT
WITH OUR UPOLU MANTRA OF-- WHAT
IS IT AGAIN, COACH?
OUR MANTRA IS HONOR, LOYALTY,
INTEGRITY.
AND I THINK OF ALL THE
REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS,
BRANDON
DEVIATES MOST FROM OUR MANTRA.
FROM THE FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
HE PLOTTED A LIE THAT INVOLVED
STACEY AND CHRISTINE AGAINST
MIKAYLA TO CREATE DISRUPTION.
TODAY'S CHALLENGE WAS ANOTHER
CHAMPION.
HE SAID, "MY STRATEGY WAS TO
PREVENT YOU, EDNA, FROM WINNING
IMMUNITY."
HOW IS THAT CONSISTENT WITH
HONOR AND INTEGRITY?
Jeff: BRANDON, WHAT'S IT
LIKE TO HEAR THIS MOMENTS
BEFORE
WE VOTE SOMEBODY TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND?
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE ANYTHING
NEGATIVE TO SAY ABOUT EDNA.
SHE'S MISCONSTREWED A LOT OF
THINGS.
SHE'S BEEN INACCURATE --
I HAVE TO SAY, BRENDAN, I
REMEMBER THE FIRST TRIBAL AND
THE LIE AND I REMEMBER YOU
ADMITTING IT.
AND EVERYONE HERE, INCLUDING
OUR JURY, KNOWS THAT.
Jeff: I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST SAYING SHE'S MISCONSTRUED
EVERYTHING.
WELL, MY APOLOGIES.
HONESTLY, I FEEL LIKE SHE'S
JUST
TAKING SHOTS AT ME.
I DON'T MIND BEING A PUNCHING
BAG TODAY BUT I DON'T THINK SHE
SHOULD TAKE AT MY CHARACTER
PERSONALLY.
I'VE ACTUALLY BEEN PRETTY OPEN
WITH EVERYTHING, WITH EVERY
SINGLE THING.
Jeff: SO, WOULD IT HURT
YOUR FEELINGS IF YOU WERE VOTE
OUT TONIGHT?
ABSOLUTELY.
AND AFTER HEARING THE THINGS
THAT EDNA SAID ABOUT ME, IT
HURT
MY FEELINGS A LOT BECAUSE I'VE
NEVER HAD A NEGATIVE THING TO
SAY ABOUT EDNA, DESPITE THE
FACT
THAT SHE'S RUNNING AROUND THE
TRIBE AND PLANTING SEEDS IN
PEOPLE'S MINDS.
Jeff: EDNA--
TO CLARIFY, I WASN'T PLANTING
SEEDS.
I AM NOT FABRICATING THE EVENTS
THAT HAPPENED.
THEY WANT.
I DIDN'T MAKE ONE OF THOSE
THINGS UP.
Jeff: SOPHIE, TAKE ME
THROUGH THE DIFFICULTY OF
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
NOW THAT YOU ARE WITH A GROUP
OF
PEOPLE THAT YOU HAVE BEEN
TOGETHER FOR 32 DAYS?
RIGHT.
AS EVERYBODY SAID, WE'RE A
FAMILY.
WE HAVE ALL THIS UNITY.
WE HAVE ALL THIS LOYALTY.
BUT AS SAVAII HAS BEEN
REMINDING
US, IT'S GOING TO END SOON, AND
I THINK TODAY IS THAT DAY THAT
IT'S ENDING.
Jeff: ALBERT, WHERE DO YOU
SIT ON THIS?
WELL, IT GETS DIFFICULT WHEN
YOU GOAT THIS POINT YOU KNOW
BECAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE
CONTRIBUTED TO US GETTING HERE,
BUT WHEN YOU LOOK AT THAT CORE,
IT ALWAYS STARTS TO GET THINNER
AND THINNER THE DEEPER GO INTO
THIS GAME AND WE'RE MAKING A
DECISION BETWEEN HOW THE GAME
IS
PLAYED OUT AND THE PROMISES
THAT
WERE MADE EARLY ON.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO THE VOTE.
COACH HAS THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
RICK, YOU'RE UP.
BRANDON, I KNOW YOU CAME OUT
HERE TO CLEANSE YOUR FAMILY
NAME.
YOU'RE NOT DOING A VERY GOOD
JOB
AT IT.
I'M SORRY.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, EDNA.
BRANDON.
EDNA.
TWO VOTES EDNA, ONE VOTE
BRANDON.
EDNA.
THREE VOTES EDNA, ONE VOTE
BRANDON.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT, EDNA.
THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
EDNA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO I'D.
GOOD LUCK.
THANKS, JEFF.
Jeff: WELL, FROM THE
BEGINNING, YOU'VE SAID IT WOULD
BE THE FIVE OF YOU.
NOW WHAT?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
WE KNOW THAT WE CAN GO AT IT
WITH HONOR, LOYALTY, AND
INTEGRITY.
THAT IS NOT TRUE.
DON'T YOU LIE TO ME.
THEY TOLD US.
WILL YOU ( BLEEP ) LET ME
FINISH.
I DO NOT CARE A SINGLE THING
ABOUT HONOR AND INTEGRITY.
EDNA THINKS SHE MAY HAVE IT.
NO WAY.
OZZY?
YEAH.
SORERY TO SCARE YOU.
IT'S EDNA.
HEY, EDNA.
I WAS VERY DISAPPOINTED TO
SEE COACH WRITE DOWN MY NAME.
HIS CONSTANT FEAR OF LOOKING
LIKE HE'S BETRAYED THE TRIBE
HAS
MADE ME FEEL BETRAYED BY HIM.