Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": ON DAY 19, THE TWO
TRIBES MERGED.
DROP YOUR BUFFS.
YES!
Jeff: AND OZZY RETURNED
FROM REDEMPTION ISLAND AND WAS
BACK IN THE GAME.
I'M ALIVE.
BUT AT THIS POINT IT'S A
DEAD-LOCKED 6-6 VOTE.
Jeff: TO GET INFORMATION TO
BREAK THE TIE, COCHRAN PROMISED
TO SPY ON THE OLD UPOLU.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR ME TO WORK
MY MAGIC, BECOME THE DOUBLE
AGENT, INFILTRATE UPOLU.
Jeff: BUT COACH SEDUCED HIM
INTO JUMPING SHIP.
WHERE AM I SLEEPING TONIGHT?
RIGHT BETWEEN ME AND EDNA.
Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE THERE WERE TWO
WINNERS.
DAWN AND OZZY SAFE AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL--
IT'S FOR WHITNEY.
Jeff: OZZY GAVE HIS
IMMUNITY IDOL TO WHITNEY.
FIRST VOTE.
BUT WHITNEY DIDN'T RECEIVE ANY
VOTES.
WE ARE TIED.
WE WILL REVOTE.
ON THE REVOTE COCHRAN BLINDED
SIDES HIS OLD ALLIANCE.
SENDING KEITH TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
KEITH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW THE FORMER UPOLU TRIBE PLUS
COCHRAN HAS TAKEN OVER THE GAME.
THAT WAS, WITHOUT QUESTION, THE
BIGGEST MOVE IN THE GAME THUS
FAR AND THIS GAME IS FAR FROM
OVER.
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
IT HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH,
LIKE, GETTING BACK AT YOU OR
HURTING ANYBODY.
IT WAS-- I DIDN'T-- YOU KNOW,
I'VE BEEN OBSESSED WITH THIS FOR
11 YEARS.
TO HAVE MY FATE DECIDED BY
PICKING A STONE OUT OF A BAG.
COCHRAN, YOU TOTALLY SCREWED
ME OVER.
AND, ALSO,-- I'M JUST TRYING TO
TALK TO HIM ALONE.
I'D RATHER--
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TELL HIM.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
NOBODY'S BEING AGGRESSIVE WITH
HIM OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
COME ON.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE AGGRESSIVE.
I KNOW--
OZZY-- OZZY-- OZZY--
IT'S JUST ME AND HIM.
WE'RE NOT, LIKE, GANGSTERS OUT
HERE, MAN.
I MEAN, YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND,
LIKE, I PUT MY ASS ON THE LINE
FOR YOU DIRECTLY, PERSONALLY,
AND YOU JUST TURNED TARND AND
YOU JUST STABBED ME IN THE BACK
SO HARD.
THIS WAS SELF-INTEREST,
SELF-PRESERVATION
COCHRAN SAID IT WAS ALL ABOUT
SELF-PRESERVATION, AND SURE,
THAT'S THE EASY WAY OUT.
THAT'S HOW A WEANER PLAYS.
I HOPE YOU MAKE IT FAR.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
YOU'RE A COWARD.
YOU'RE A POOR EXCUSE FOR A MANY.
DON'T ( BLEEP ) ME EVER AGAIN.
OKAY.
UHM SO YOU'RE-- YOU'RE THE
VOTE?
YEAH, YEAH.
AND YOU REALIZE KEITH AND I--
KEITH AND I SAVED YOU THREE
TIMES.
YOU WERE ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
KEITH AND I SAVED YOU THREE
TIMES.
AND THAT'S WHAT YOU ( BLEEP )
DO.
IT WASN'T-- AGAINST YOU.
REALLY?
IT WASN'T AGAINST ME.
NO.
AND THAT'S WHAT YOU DO?
YOU THROW THE WHOLE ( BLEEP )
TRIBE UNDER THE BUS, AND NOW WE
BASICALLY MIGHT AS WELL JUST--
WE'RE GOING TO BE KNOCKED OUT
ONE BY ONE.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT TO LEARN,
BUDDY.
YOU DISGUST ME.
COCHRAN.
JOIN US, BUDDY.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU OKAY?
GETTA A FROSTY RECEPTION,
WHICH IS UNDERSTANDABLE.
I'M KIND OF HAVING MIX
EMOTIONS RIGHT NOW.
ON THE ONE HAND, I'M GLAD I KIND
OF STOOD UP TO THE PEOPLE WHO
REPEATEDLY REFERRED TO ME AS
INDECISIVE, WEAK, EVEN ANNOYING.
BUT IT'S KIND OF A WEIRD
BALANCING ACT I'M DOING RIGHT
NOW BETWEEN THE UPOLU MEMBERS
WHO ARE NOW EMBRACING ME MORE
THAN EVER.
DON'T FEEL GUILTY.
YOU DIDN'T DO A THING WRONG.
AND MY FORMER TRIBEMATES WHO
SEEM TO REALLY, REALLY HATE MY
GUTS.
PIECE OF ( BLEEP ) NERD.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
WE PULLED OFF AN AMAZING FEAT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL LAST NIGHT.
OUR TRIBE OF UPOLU MEMBERS STOOD
SIX STRONG.
AGAINST ALL ODDS, AND IT'S CAUSE
FOR CELEBRATION.
IT'S CAUSE FOR WALKING THE
BEACH.
SAYING A LITTLE PRAYER.
STARTING THE DAY OFF RIGHT.
DO A LITTLE THI CHI.
I FEEL LIKE IF I CAN JUST BE
CONFIDENT AND NOT ARROGANT, I
CAN BE HUMBLE, BUT NOT WEAK, I
THINK I HAVE A GOOD SHOT AT
GOING ALL THE WAY.
IN TERMS OF, LIKE, CHALLENGE,
OZZY IS OBVIOUSLY-- IF HE
DOESN'T WIN, IT'S PROBABLY SMART
TO GET RID OF HIM.
ON A PERSONAL LEVEL JIM.
REALLY?
"SURVIVOR" CAN BE REALLY CUT
THROAT AND YOU HAVE TO TRUST
PEOPLE AT CERTAIN POINTS AND
THOSE PEOPLE CAN TURN AROUND AND
JUST STICK A KNIFE RIGHT IN YOUR
GUT, AND THAT'S WHAT COCHRAN
DID.
SO MY TOTAL STRATEGY IS GONE.
I HAVE NOTHING MORE I CAN DO.
I'M JUST GOING TO KEEP FIGHTING.
AND GOING TO BUST MY ASS TODAY
AT THE CHALLENGE, AND I'M JUST
GOING TO KEEP ON WINNING UNTIL
THERE'S NO ONE LEFT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
DAWN AND OZZY, I'LL TAKE BACK
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACES.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
TOSS COCONUTS ATTEMPTING TO LAND
THEM IN A RING.
THE FIRST FOUR MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND.
WHERE YOU WILL CRACK COCONUTS
USING A ROCK.
YOU'LL THEN GET A MOUTH FULL OF
COCONUT WATER.
YOU'LL MAKE YOUR WAY THROUGH AN
OBSTACLE TOWER.
YOU WILL THEN EMPTY THE WATER
INTO A TUBE.
THE FIRST PERSON TO FILL THEIR
TUBE WITH COCONUT WATER WINS
IMMUNITY.
EVERYBODY ELSE, TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
MAKE SENSE?
YEAH.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT OTHER WE'LL
DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST FOUR TO LAND A COCONUT IN
THEIR RING MOVE ON TO THE NEXT
ROUND.
ONE TOSS PER ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
OH!
Jeff: DAWN LANDS ONE.
SHE'S MOVING ON.
OH!
Jeff: SOPHIE CLOSE.
NEXT ROUND.
DAWN IS MOVING ON, LOOK FOR
THREE MORE.
HE WERE WE GO.
RELEASE.
OZZY JUST MISSES.
RICK JUST MISSES.
WHITNEY LANDS ONE.
YES!
Jeff: TWO SPOTS LEFT.
JIM LANDS ONE, AND SOPHIE LANDS
ONE.
YES!
Jeff: MOVING ON TO THE NEXT
ROUND.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A SPOT ON
THE BENCH.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
GOOD JOB, GUYS, GOOD JOB.
Jeff: FOR THE FINAL ROUND
WE HAVE WHITNEY, JIM, SOPHIE,
AND DAWN.
THREE FORMER SAVAII, ONE FORMER
UPOLU.
THIS IS IT.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU GOTTA CRACK THEM OPEN THEN
GET A MOUTH FULL OF WATER AND
START HEADING OUT.
DAWN HAS HER CRACKED.
SOPHIE IS FIRST OUT WITH COCONUT
WATER.
DAWN RIGHT BEHIND.
THERE GOES JIM.
WHITNEY GETS A GOOD MOUTH FULL.
GOT TO GET OVER THAT OBSTACLE,
THEN EMPTY IT INTO THE TUBE.
GO!
GOOD JOB!
Jeff: AFTER THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, YOU WANT IMMUNITY.
THAT A GIRL, SOPH, GOOD JOB.
Jeff: SOPHIE COMING BACK
QUICKLY.
JIM QUICKLY COMING BACK.
SOPHIE SLIDING DOWN THAT POLE.
IT IS JIM AND SOPHIE NECK AND
NECK.
JIM IS PULLING AHEAD.
YOU GOT IT, JIM.
Jeff: DAWN TRYING TO STAY
IN THIS.
WHITNEY IN LAST PLACE RIGHT NOW.
KEEP IT UP, WHITT.
Jeff: JIM AND SOPHIE ARE
MAKING RUNS RIGHT NEXT TO EACH
OTHER.
DAWN NEED TO PICK UP THE PACE.
SHE IS FALLING OUT OF THIS.
THE MORE COCONUT WATER YOU CAN
GET IN YOUR MOUTH, THE FASTER
YOU WILL FINISH, AND THAT'S WHAT
THIS IS GOING TO COME DOWN TO.
JIM GETTING CLOSER.
SOPHIE TRYING TO CATCH JIM.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO DO IT.
GO TO BATTLE, SOPH.
Jeff: OPENING THE DOOR FOR
JIM.
COULD JIM DO IT RIGHT HERE?
NO.
JIM, JUST SHORT.
OPENING THE DOOR FOR SOPHIE.
SHE'S GOT TO PICK IT UP.
YOU GOTTA MOVE, GIRL!
COME ON, SOPHIE, YOU CAN DO
IT.
THAT A GIRL, SOPH.
Jeff: SOPHIE ALMOST
VOMITING.
CONTROL YOURSELF, SOPH.
Jeff: SOPHIE ALMOST
SPITTING IT IT IT UP.
HERE COMES JIM.
THAT DOOR IS BACK OPEN.
SOPHIE CAN'T KEEP IT DOWN.
SHE LOSES AN ENTIRE ROUND ON
THAT.
HUGE SETBACK FOR SOPHIE.
JIM JUMPS ONCE AGAIN,
CELEBRATING ALREADY.
JIM WINS IMMUNITY!
( APPLAUSE )
JIM, COME ON OVER.
GOOD JOB, MAN.
WAY TO GO, JIM!
GOOD JOB, JIM!
Jeff: CONGRATULATIONS.
JIM, SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
GOOD JOB, JIM.
NICE WORK, JIM.
SO THERE'S NO IF, ANDS, BUTS
ABOUT IT.
IT'S GOING TO BE SIX VOTES
TOWARD OZZY.
WE JUST HAVE TO GO FOR IT, DUDE.
HOW MANY CHANCES DO YOU GET TO
VOTE HIM OUT OF THIS GAME?
APPARENTLY TWO.
OH, YEAH.
I DON'T WANT TO GO.
YOU KNOW.
THAT'S REALLY ALL I CAN OFFER IS
JUST WHO I AM.
YEAH.
OZZY KNOWS THAT THERE'S A GOOD
CHANCE HE COULD GET VOTED OUT
TONIGHT.
AND THERE'S A HUGE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN YESTERDAY WHEN HE HELD
ALL THE CARDS AND THE COKENESS
THAT HE HAD, AND TODAY.
THAT'S IT.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO LEAVE,
MAN.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE,
EITHER.
I ACTUALLY APPRECIATE OZZY'S
HUMILITY.
IF IT'S FAKE, IF IT'S TOO LATE,
OR IF IT'S JUST BORNE OUT OF
DESPERATION, THAT'S OKAY.
SOME OF THE GREATEST INSPIRATION
IS BORNE OF DESPERATION, MARCUS
ARILLUOUS ONCE SAID.
BUT AT THIS POINT, IT'S TOO
LITTLE, TOO LATE.
IT WAS A GOOD RIDE.
OH, YOU'RE COMING BACK.
I'M CONVINCED OF THAT.
I'LL TRY.
COME ON, MAN.
COACH, YOU GONNA TRY THE
BUNGALOW?
JUST TRY IT.
THERE'S A PILLOW, TOO.
I THINK-- DON'T YOU THINK YOU
SHOULD HAVE A BLANKET AND A
PILLOW TONIGHT, NOW THAT THE
HAPPINESS IS--
I THINK THAT WOULD BE
AWESOME.
WE GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
THERE'S REALLY FOUR SAVAII
MEMBERS.
JIM HAS IMMUNITY.
OZZY, MYSELF, OR WHITNEY ARE
GOING TO REDEMPTION.
WE EITHER HAVE TO REALLY STAY
LOYAL TO THE FINAL FOUR OF US
AND JUST GO DOWN IN FLAMES OR
I'M GOING TO NEED TO CONSIDER
FLIPPING AND VOTING WITH THE
UPOLU TRIBE.
THAT'S A LITTLE PILLOW.
IT WILL BE LIKE A DAY AT THE
SPA.
I'M EASILY THE MOST HATED
PERSON IN THIS CAMP RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE I SPEAK MY MIND.
EVERYTHING I SAID ABOUT COCHRAN
IS TRUE.
RIGHT, TOTALLY.
HE'S THE POOREST EXCUSE FOR A
MAN THEY KNOW.
I TOLD HIM HE DISGUSTED ME.
HE DOES.
I COULD NEVER HAVE EVER
THROWN MY TRIBE UNDER THE BUS
LIKE COCHRAN DID TO US.
I CALL A COWARD A COWARD.
THAT'S ME.
BECAUSE I'M NOT A COWARD.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
I HAVE NOTHING.
HERE'S WHAT I GOT.
I'M GOING TO DO IT.
DON'T SAY NO.
JUST LISTEN TO WHAT I SAY.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THE
NECKLACE TONIGHT AND SAY,UN
WHAT?
THERE ARE 11 PEOPLE HERE.
AND 10 OF US HAVE PLAYED WITH
COMPLETE HONOR, STUCK WITH THEIR
TRIBE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON OUT OF
THE 11 PEOPLE HERE THAT'S
TURNED.
YOU GUYS STILL HAVE A 6-4
ADVANTAGE ON US, BUT I'M ASKING
YOU TONIGHT TO VOTE FOR COCHRAN.
I THINK WE'VE GOT A SHOT FOR TWO
PEOPLE TONIGHT, ESPECIALLY IF
THEY ALL GO IN THINKING VOTING
OZZY.
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN THEY DON'T
GET A CHANCE TO TALK AND THE
LAST WORDS THAT THEY HEAR ARE
"VOTE COCHRAN" WITH A PRETTY
COMPELLING CASE.
IT'S CRAZY, MAN.
IF I DON'T GO TONIGHT, I GO
TOMORROW NIGHT.
IF I DON'T GO TOMORROW NIGHT, I
GO THE NEXT NIGHT.
I REALLY DON'T HAVE MANY NIGHTS
LEFT HERE.
SO MY HOPE SICAN GIVE A ROUSING
ENOUGH SPEECH AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TO GET A COUPLE OF THEM TO FLIP
OVER TO COCHRAN.
I NEED TWO OF THEM TO GO FOR IT.
THAT'S ALL I NEED, TWO OF THOSE
SEVEN PEOPLE TO VOTE FOR
COCHRAN.
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN, WE GOT A
GAME.
JIM, ALL I GOTTA SAY YOU WANT
TO MAKE ME CRY RIGHT NOW.
EVERYTHING'S PRETTY SURREAL TO
ME RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN, IF JIM HONESTLY GIVES ME
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE TONIGHT, I
DON'T-- I'LL BE-- I'LL FEEL LIKE
I'M DREAMING.
KNOWING JIM, I BELIEVE THAT IF
HE SAYS HE'S GOING TO GIVE ME
THE NECKLACE, I BELIEVE HE WILL.
WHO KNOWS WHALE HAPPEN IN THIS
GAME?
WHO REALLY KNOWS?
AND I'M NEVER GOING TO GIVE UP
AS LONG AS I LIVE.
AND CERTAINLY NOT HERE ON
"SURVIVOR."
Jeff: SO THE THEME OF THE
LAST TWO TRIBAL COUNCILS HAS
BEEN BIG MOVES.
COCHRAN, WHAT WAS THE REACTION
TO YOUR HUGE MOVE AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL?
THE REACTION WAS
UNDERSTANDABLY KIND OF CHILLY, A
LUKEWARM RECEPTION, TO PUT IT
MILDLY.
Jeff: WHO FROM YOUR TRIBE
BARKED THE LOUDEST?
JIM IS IS GENERALLY A PRETTY
LOUD GUY SO IT WASN'T SURPRISING
THAT HE WAS ONE OF THE MORE
VOCAL CRITICS OF MY DECISION AND
BASICALLY DIDN'T WANT TO HEAR
ANYTHING I HAD TO SAY IN SUPPORT
OF MY DECISION.
Jeff: JIM.
I SAID SOME THINGS THAT WERE
IMMATURE.
THIS IS JUST A GAME BUT DITAKE
IT A LITTLE BIT PERSONAL?
YES, I DID.
Jeff: COCHRAN HOW DID YOU
DEAL WITH THE REACTIONS?
MAINLY BY STAYING SILENT AND
LISTENING.
IT WAS A PERSONAL DECISION.
I VIEWED IT AS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
TAKE CONTROL OF MY OWN FATE IN
THIS GAME TO PLAY WITH THE SORT
OF GROUP OF PEOPLE I WANTED TO
PLAY WITH.
I DON'T MEAN ANY DISRESPECT TO
MY FORMER TRIBE MATES.
I KNOW IT SOUNDED HORRENDOUS.
YEAH, IT CAN DID.
YEAH.
DIDN'T MENTALLY PREPARE FOR
THIS FOR 11 YEARS TO HAVE MY
FATE DECIDED BY DRAWING A BAG.
THE LAST TIME PEOPLE DRAW ROCKS
WAS IN SEASON 4 BECAUSE PEOPLE
REALIZED THAT'S NOT HOW YOU PLAY
"SURVIVOR."
IT'S TAKING CONTROL OF MY OWN
FATE.
I CAN ADD ONE THING THAT I
THINK WILL ROUND IT OUT?
I SAVED COCHRAN IN THE FIRST
VOTE.
I SAVED COCHRAN IN THE SECOND
KEITH, WHITNEY, AND I, SAVED HIM
IN THE THIRD VOTE, AND OZZY
SAVED HIM AT REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AND I'VE GOTTEN TO KNOW THE
UPOLU TRIBE THE LAST COUPLE OF
DAYS AND THERE'S NOT A SINGLE
ONE OF THEM THAT WOULD LET
SOMEBODY FIGHT THEIR FIGHTS FOR
THEM AND NOT SOMEBODY WHO WOULD
DO SOMETHING SO DISHONORABLE.
I THINK PROOF IS IN THE
PUDDING.
IF YOU REMEMBER FROM LAST
TRIBAL
IT WAS A WAY DIFFERENT TONE, WE
WERE BEING MADE FUN OF TO PLAY
WITH INTEGRITY.
IT'S KIND OF POETIC JUSTICE, TO
BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT FEELING OF
GETTING TIRED OF BEING MADE FUN
OF.
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
THE SMALLER PEOPLE DON'T HAVE TO
TAKE IT ANYMORE.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE BULLIED
AROUND.
I JUST-- I JUST WANT TO NOTE,
DID I EVER BERATE YOU.
THE WHOLE TRIBE IS STANDING
BEHIND COCHRAN.
PERIOD.
I FEEL LIKE I'M BEING
VILLINIZED.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW, DIEVER
MAKE YOU FEEL LIKE YOU WERE
SMALL?
YOU MADE ME FEEL LIKE I WAS
SMALL BY BASES YOUR FIRST
SEVERAL VOTES AGAINST ME AND
TRYING TO GET PEOPLE VOTE ME OUT
ON THE BASIS OF MY WEAKNESS.
Jeff: SO, JIM, VERY
POWERFUL SPOT RIGHT NOW FOR YOU.
SITTING WITH IMMUNITY.
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
I KNOW, I WIN IMMUNITY.
I IMMEDIATELY THINK I'M GOING TO
GIVE IT TO OZZY TONIGHT.
Jeff: WHY WOULD IT MAKE
SENSE TO GIVE OZZY YOUR
NECKLACE?
I HAVE GOTTEN TO KNOW THESE
GUYS.
THEY CONSISTENTLY SAY HONOR,
HONOR, HONOR.
I KNOW THEY RESPECT US AS
COMPETITORS.
I KNOW THEY SEE I HAVE A WARRIOR
HEART AND A WARRIOR SOLE SOUL
AND THERE ARE 10 OF US THAT HAVE
NOT WAIVERRED FROM OUR TRIBE
ONCE.
THERE'S ONE PERSON WHO HAS.
TODAY AS ONE VOICE WE CAN SEND A
MESSAGE TO ANYBODY WHO EVER WILL
PLAY "SURVIVOR" THAT YOU CAN GO
THROUGH THIS GAME HONORABLY, AND
IF YOU'RE A TURNCOAT YOU GOT NO
PLACE IN MY TRIBE.
YOU CAN SAY THAT RIGHT NOW BY
VOTING OFF COCHRAN.
Jeff: COACH, JIM'S NOT
GIVING UP.
YEAH, I MEAN, ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, JIM STARTS TALKING ABOUT
WARRIOR THIS AND WARRIOR THAT
AND I STAND UP A LITTLE BIT
STRAIGHTER AND LISTEN WITH A
MORE ATTENTIVE EAR.
Jeff: IF YOU VOTED OUT
COCHRAN TONIGHT, WOULD IT CHANGE
THE GAME?
I THINK IT WOULD SEND A
MESSAGE TO EVERYTHING THAT IF
YOU STICK UP FOR YOURSELF,
YOU'RE GOING TO GET SCREWED.
AND I'M NOT-- I'M NOT GOING TO
SEE THAT HAPPEN.
DOES VOTING COCHRAN OUT
CHRONICLE THE NAME GAME?
NO, IT DOESN'T.
IT TAKE ONE PERSON OUT.
YOU STILL HAVE A 6-4 LEAD.
IT GIVES THESE GUYS AN
OPPORTUNITY TO REALLY SAY BEYOND
THIS GAME WHAT IS THIS GAME
ABOUT?
Jeff: SOPHIE, WHOEVER YOU
LEAVE IN THE GAME IS AS
IMPORTANT AS WHO YOU GOT RID OF.
I THINK RIGHT NOW, THERE'S--
THERE'S NO GOOD VOTE BECAUSE
WE'RE NOT ELIMINATING SOMEBODY
FOR SURE.
LET ME JUST THROW SOMETHING
OUT THERE.
WHEN I'M AT REDEMPTION, I'M NOT
FEEDING 11 PEOPLE.
I'M FEEDING MYSELF.
I'M GOING TO BE FULL.
I'M GOING TO BE WELL RESTED.
I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT EVERYBODY SCRAMBLING.
EVENTUALLY, THESE NUMBERS ARE
GOING TO START TO CHANGE, AND
YOU WILL ONLY HAVE YOURSELVES TO
VOTE OUT.
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS, IT'S
GOING TO GET A LITTLE FUNKY.
Jeff: AND, OZZY, IF IT IS
YOU TONIGHT, I'M GUESSING YOUR
MESSAGE WILL BE A LITTLE
DIFFERENT THAN "I'VE HAD A GREAT
TIME."
MY MESSAGE IS I WILL BE BACK.
I WILL BE PUTTING EVERY LAST
OUNCE OF MY SOUL INTO
REDEMPTION.
I HOPE TO SEE ALL OF YOU COMING
THROUGH THERE, AND I'LL MAKE YOU
A NICE FISH, AND I'LL SEND YOU
ON YOUR WAY.
Jeff: SO, BEFORE WE GET TO
THE VOTE, ONE PRESSING
QUESTION-- JIM, YOU HAVE THE
IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
AS YOU KNOW, YOU CAN ASSIGN IT
TO SOMEBODY ELSE, IF YOU WANT
TO.
OR KEEP IT FOR YOURSELF.
I'M GOING TO KEEP IT TONIGHT.
Jeff: YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR
JIM.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
WHITNEY, YOU'RE UP.
I JUST REALLY DON'T LIKE YOU.
YOU HAVE BEEN TRYING TO GET
ME OUT SINCE WEEK ONE SO I DON'T
THINK IT'S THAT INAPPROPRIATE
FOR ME TO BE VOTING FOR YOU.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NO WOULD BE THE TIME TO
DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE.
OZZY.
COCHRAN.
TWO VOTES OZZY.
OZZY.
THREE VOTES OZZY.
TWO VOTES COCHRAN.
OZZY.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES OZZY.
TWO VOTES COCHRAN.
OZZY.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES OZZY, TWO
VOTES COCHRAN.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC." OZZY
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU GUYS FELL FOR MY MASTER
PLAN!
LET'S TRY THIS ONE MORE TIME,
JEFF.
Jeff: OZZY, ONCE AGAIN, THE
TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND ONCE AGAIN, YOU WILL HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT.
Jeff: GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION.
GOOD LUCK.
WELL, FOR 22 DAYS, THIS GAME HAS
BEEN UNPREDICTABLE.
FOR WHITNEY, DAWN, AND JIM, YOU
JUST GOTTA HOPE IT STAYS THAT
WAY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
I PLAYED A REALLY HARD, HARD
GAME.
I PLAYED AND MADE BIG MOVES.
AND I'M PRETTY MUCH PROUD OF
WHAT I DID.
I TOOK BIG RISKS.
THEY DIDN'T WORK OUT IN MY
FAVOR.
BUT YOU GOTTA TAKE BIG RISKS TO
GET BIG REWARD AND I'M READY TO
DO REALLY WELL AT REDEMPTION.
DUDE.
TOTALLY.
BY COCHRAN, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
WHEN PEOPLE COME THROUGH, I'M
GOING TO TREAT THEM REALLY NICE,
AND THEN I'M GOING TO SEND THEM
PACKING.
I JUST GOT TO REDEMPTION LAST
NIGHT.
THIS IS MY FIRST CHANCE JUST
TOOK EXPLORE THE REEF.
AND THE REEF OUT HERE IS
MAGNIFICENT.
WHERE THE REEF DROPS OFF, IT
DROPS OFF PROBABLY A SOLID 20 TO
30 FEET.
AND THEN FROM THERE IT JUST GOES
STRAIGHT DOWN.
THE TIDE RIPS OUT REALLY HARD
AND THERE ARE BIG WAVES BUT
THAT'S WHERE YOU GET BIG FISH
HANGING OUT.
HA-HA!
YES!
BIGGEST FISH I'VE EVER CAUGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO BE EATING WELL
TONIGHT.
RIGHT NOW AND TONIGHT.
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE-- IT'S GOT
TO BE, LIKE, 15 POUNDS.
SO MUCH MEAT.
SUSHIMI ON "SURVIVOR."
ME, TOO.
I'M HAPPY TO BE HERE.
I WISH I WAS IN THE GAME, BUT
I'M JUST AS EXCITED TO BE HERE.
I WONDER WHAT THEY'RE EATING
TODAY?
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JIM, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO STAND ON A VERY NARROW
BEAM WHILE BALANCING A BALL ON A
WOODEN BOW.
AT A CERTAIN POINT, YOU'LL MOVE
EVEN FURTHER DOWN THE BEAM,
MAKING IT MORE DIFFICULT.
IF AT ANY POINT THE BALL DROPS
OR YOU FALL OFF THE BEAM, YOU'RE
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY AND IS SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
THERE IS A TWIST TO TODAY'S
CHALLENGE.
IF YOU ARE SO CONFIDENT THAT
YOUR ONE IN 10 SPOT IN THIS GAME
FOR $1 MILLION IS SECURE THAT
YOU DON'T NEED IMMUNITY TONIGHT
YOU CAN SIT THIS CHALLENGE OUT
AND INSTEAD YOU CAN FEAST.
OH, MY GOD!
OH!
Jeff: ONE OF THE BIGGEST
CRAVINGS WHEN YOU'RE OUT HERE
ARE SWEETS.
YOU HAVE PASTRIES AND ICED
COFFEE.
THIS IS A CHANCE TO SATISFY THAT
CRAVING.
I GOTTA PICK UP ON THE OBVIOUS.
EVERYBODY IS CELEBRATING EXCEPT
COACH.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU JUST GOT THE
WORST NEWS OF YOUR LIFE.
YEAH, I'M JUST KNOW-- I WANT
TO COMPETE TODAY.
Jeff: COMPETE.
THERE ARE SEVEN PEOPLE WHO
DON'T NEED TO COMPETE.
Jeff: LET ME DO THE OBVIOUS
MATH.
THE THREE FORMER SAVAII FEEL IN
TROUBLE AND I'M GUESSING ARE
GOING TO PLAY AND UPOLU AND
COCHRAN ARE THINKING THEY MAY
NOT NEED IT.
THE THING ISRY WITH A FAMILY
AND WE STICK TOGETHER AND WE'RE
UNIFIED IN OUR STANCE.
Jeff: WHO HERE IS GOING TO
COMPETE?
JIM, DAWN, AND WHITNEY.
NOT SURPRISING.
Jeff: UPOLU TRIBE AND
COCHRAN, TAKE A SPOT HERE.
DAWN, JIM, WHITNEY, WE'LL DRAW
FOR SPOTS AND GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, DAWN, WHITNEY, JIM.
THE ONLY THREE PARTICIPATING IN
THIS IMMUNITY CHALLENGE TAKE
YOUR SPOTS.
ONE FOOT IN THE FIRST SECTION,
ONE FOOT IN THE SECOND SECTION.
EVERYBODY ELSE GET READY TO EAT.
THE EATING WILL END WHEN THE
CHALLENGE IS OVER.
PUT YOUR BALL IN YOUR BOW.
IF YOUR BALL FALLS OFF OR YOU
FALL OFF, YOU ARE OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY LOOKS GOOD AND THIS
CHALLENGE IS ON, START EATING.
QUITE A CONTRAST.
WE HAVE SEVEN PEOPLE CHOWING
DOWN, ALL KINDS OF SWEETS.
THERE ARE THREE PEOPLE LEFT FROM
A TRIBE FIGHTING FOR SECURITY
TONIGHT WHILE THE OTHER SEVEN
ENJOY THE REWARDS BEING THE
TRIBE THAT IS RIGHT NOW THE
DOMINANT ONE.
COACH, STILL WISHING YOU WERE
PAYMENTING IN THE CHALLENGE?
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
STAY THERE, DAWN.
WOW.
THAT'S CREAMY.
OH, MAN, THIS IS RIDUNKOLOUS.
THIS MUFFIN LOOKS SO GREAT.
Jeff: AFTER 24 DAYS,
BRANDON, HOW GOOD DOES THAT
TASTE?
I DON'T WANT TO TALK.
I WANT TO EAT.
Jeff: TRY TO BLOCK OUT THE
SOUNDS YOU'RE HEARING AS BEST
YOU CAN.
JIM, DROPS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
JIM HAS NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY
TONIGHT.
I KNOW!
Jeff: IT IS NOW DOWN TO
DAWN AND WHITNEY.
WHITNEY AND DAWN, YOU'RE
DOING AWESOME.
YEAH, PLEASE, STAY FOCUSED.
I'LL STAY SO YOU CAN EAT.
Jeff: SO, DAWN, LET ME GET
THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE SAYING YOU'RE GOING TO
FIGHT TO STAY IN THIS CHALLENGE
AS LONG AS YOU CAN SO THESE
GUYIES CAN EAT AS MUCH AS
POSSIBLE?
YEAH, I REALLY FEEL LIKE IT'S
ONE TRIBE RIGHT NOW.
I GUESS GETTHAT THERE ARE THREE
OF US FROM THE FORMER SAVAII
TRIBE BUT IT'S NOT THAT WAY.
EAT AS MUCH AS YOU CAN.
DAWN HAS BEEN INCREDIBLE.
ABSOLUTELY, I'D LIKE TO
SECOND THAT.
STAY THERE, DAWN.
SHE'S--
Jeff: DAWN WITH A LITTLE
BIT OF A SLIP AND A NICE
RECOVERY.
FIVE MORE SECONDS LEFT IN THIS
ROUND AND YOU WILL STEP DOWN.
FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
YOU'RE DONE.
GRAB THE BALL.
YOU'RE SAFE.
YOU'LL NOW MOVE DOWN TO THE NEXT
SECTION OF THIS BEAM.
THIS IS GOING TO INCREASE THE
DIFFICULTY BECAUSE IT IS VERY
NARROW.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
REALLY BALANCE WHILE BALANCING
THE BALL.
PLACE YOUR BALL BACK ON YOUR BO
BOW.
FIND SOME PLACE THAT FEELS LIKE
CENTER.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO REALLY
CONCENTRATE NOW.
VERY LITTLE ROOM FOR ERROR HERE.
THE SLIGHTEST SHIFT IN YOUR
BALANCE WILL KNOCK YOU OFF OF
THIS BEAM.
YOU GIRLS ARE DOING GOOD.
Jeff: THE EATING HAS SLOWED
DOWN AT THE TABLE.
I THINK I'M OUT.
Jeff: LOTS OF FULL BELLIES.
THE WINNER OF THIS IS GUARANTEED
A ONE IN NINE SHOT AT THE MONEY.
24 DAYS, YOU DO NOT WANT TO GO
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND RIGHT NOW.
STAY STRONG.
Jeff: DAWN WITH A WOBBLE,
CAN SHE RECOVER?
STAY STRONG.
Jeff: AMAZING JOB!
OH, YES!
AWESOME, AWESOME RECOVERY.
SO, AWESOME!
YOU CAN TELL WHO BRANDON
LIKES MORE.
Jeff: DAWN COULDN'T HANG ON
ANYMORE.
WHITNEY WINS IMMUNITY.
IS SAFE AT NIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WHITNEY, COME ON OVER.
GOOD JOB, WHITT.
GOOD JOB, WHITNEY!
( APPLAUSE )
WAY TO GO.
YOU DID IT.
Jeff: WHITNEY IS SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU CANNOT VOTE HER OUT OF THIS
GAME.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS VULNERABLE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
FINISH WHAT'S IN YOUR MOUTH AND
HEAD OUT.
PERSONALLY, I DEPARTMENT
REALLY LIKE THE WAY WE TREATED
DAWN AT THE CHALLENGE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE A LITTLE TOO
INCLUSIVE WITH HER.
I WANT TO NIP THIS IN THE BUD AS
SOON AS I CAN.
HEY, BRO!
DRAGON SLAYER.
LOOK AT THIS GUY, MAN.
WHAT IS UP?
YEAH!
COCHRAN, WHAT IS UP, MAN?
WE ARE SEEING THIS SIDE OF YOU,
BABY
( APPLAUSE ).
YEAH!
COCHRAN RIGHT NOW IS PLAYING
THE MOST BRILLIANT THIRD-PLACE
GAME IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
EVERY ONE OF THOSE NINE PEOPLE
WOULD LOVE TO TAKE COCHRAN TO
THE END.
COCHRAN, YOU ARE THE MAN,
BABY!
I THINK HE LOOKS LIKE A STUD.
NOW YOU'RE FULLY INCORPORATED
INTO OUR TRIBE.
COCHRAN AIN'T GOING NOWHERE.
BUT IT'S NOT LOOKING GOOD FOR
ME.
I AM 100% GOING TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
UNLESS I MAKE SOME MOVES RIGHT
NOW.
SO HERE'S HOW I SEE IT.
WE'VE GOT COACH WITH COCHRAN,
EDNA, AND BRANDON UNDERNEATH
THEM, AND RICK WHO HAS GIVEN HIS
WORD TO COACH, AND RICK IS THE
ONLY GUY WHO PROBABLY WOULD
NEVER GO BACK ON HIS WORD.
WE HAVE YOU TWO, THE ONLY TWO
PEOPLE WHO AREN'T DRINKING THE
COOL AID AND IN THE CULT, AND WE
HAVE DAWN, WHITT ME, AND ME OVER
HERE.
WE HAVE THE FIVE OF US VOTING
EDNA-- THIS WOULD BE MY PLAN.
FIVE OF US VOTING EDNA--
JIM APPROACHED ME AND SOPHIE
AND TOLD US, LISTEN, I HAVE A
PLAN, GET RID OF EDNA.
AND HE J.D. DREW UP SOMETHING
THAT WAS PRETTY CREATIVE AND
OUTSIDE THE BOX, SO TO SPEAK.
I NEED TO ENTERTAIN JIM'S OFFER
BECAUSE I HAVE A MUCH BETTER
PLAN THAN ANYTHING HE COULD
OFFER ME RIGHT NOW.
I KIND OF LIKE THE BUCKET.
YEAH, RIGHT.
I THINK DAWN, EVEN THOUGH SHE
DOESN'T SEEM AS OVERTLY
DANGEROUS AS JIM IS, IS MAYBE
MORE DANGEROUS THAN HIM IN A LOT
OF WAYS BECAUSE SHE'S MORE
LIKABLE, AND SHE'S SOMEBODY
THAT'S SLOWLY BUT SURELY EKING
HER WAY INTO OUR ALLIANCE.
OKAY, GOT IT?
YEAH N-
ONE BLUE SHIRT.
MINUS COCONUT.
I'VE ALWAYS SEEN MYSELF AS A
PERSON THAT CAN BRING TOGETHER
DIFFERENT TYPES OF PEOPLE.
SO FOR ME, IT ALMOST COULDN'T BE
BETTER AT THIS STAGE TO BE THAT
KIND OF PERSON BECAUSE I'M
PROBABLY A GOOD PERSON TO TRY TO
GET MYSELF IN WITH THE FORMER
UPOLU TRIBE MEMBERS AND SEE IF
THERE'S SOME WIGGLE ROOM THERE.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF WHETHER I
CAN HANG ON LONG ENOUGH.
JIM, I CAN BEAT JIM IN A LOT OF
THOSE TYPE CHALLENGES.
WE SHOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT THIS.
ALBERT, HE'S GETTING NERVOUS.
HE'S THINKING A LOT RIGHT NOW
ABOUT SWITCHING UP THE GAME AND
I THINK THOSE ARE IMPORTANT
THINGS TO THINK ABOUT IN GENERAL
"SURVIVOR" STRAIT SNEE.
BUT I'D LIKE TO STAY PRETTY
RIDGE WIDE THE PLAN.
I'D RATHER GET RID OF JIM.
HEY, MAN.
JUST BECAUSE THERE'S A GREATER
CHANCE OF PEOPLE GRAVITATING
TOWARDS DAWN.
WE'RE IN THE JUNGLE HERE.
SO I THINK AN ANALOGY TO THE
ANIMAL KINGDOM WOULD BE SUFFICE
AT THIS MOMENT.
YOU HAVE JIM BOW WHO IS LIKE A
RHINOCEROS THAT JUST COMES
CHARGING IN STRAIGHT TOWARDS
YOU.
AND THEN YOU HAVE SOMEBODY LIKE
DAWN.
SHE'S THE SERPENT ON THE SNAKE.
THEY COME SNEAKING THROUGH THE
GRASS.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE I HAVE MY
STUFF JUST IN CASE.
TODAY AT THE CHALLENGE, DAWN
WAS GETTING MOST CHEERS.
PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO GENUINELY
LIKE DAWN SO I SEE DAWN AS A
SNAKE AND JIM A RHINOCEROS.
THEY CAN BOTH KILL YOU BUT
HOPEFULLY WE'LL SEND THE RIGHT
PERSON HOME TONIGHT.
Jeff: SO, COACH, GIVEN
TODAY'S CHALLENGE AND THE FACT
THAT EVERYBODY SAT OUT, EXCEPT
FOR DAWN, JIM, AND WHITNEY, IS
IT FAIR TO ASSUME THAT SINCE
WHITNEY HAS IMMUNITY IT IS DAWN
OR JIM GOING HOME TONIGHT?
YES, ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: SOPHIE, IS IT FAIR TO
SAY THAT IF YOU HAD TO PICK ONE,
THAT JIM IS MAYBE MORE OF A
THREAT IN CHALLENGES THAN DAWN?
I THINK THEY BOTH HAVE THEIR
NICHES.
DAWN HAS SHOWN HERSELF TO BE
REALLY STRONG BUT IF I WAS
CHOOSING A ROSTER, I WOULD
CHOOSE JIM EVERY TIME.
Jeff: ALBERT, IF YOU HAD TO
CHOOSE, WOULD IT BE FAIR TO SAY
THAT DAWN MAY BE THE MORE
LIKABLE PERSON?
YEAH, I THINK IT'S VERY FAIR
TO SAY DAWN IS THE MORE LIKABLE,
AND SHE'S ALSO A TOUGH COOK
NECHALLENGES.
I MEAN, SHE'S PROVEN THAT SHE
MIGHT BE THE STRONGEST FEMALE
PLAYER ON THE SEASON.
SO, YOU KNOW, THAT WITHIN ITSELF
BEARAISE PRETTY IMPOSING
PRESENCE.
Jeff: DAWN, FOR AS
FRUSTRATING AS IT IS TO YOU AND
JIM AND WHITNEY, IS IT FAIR TO
SAY THIS IS WHAT THIS TRIBE
SHOULD DO?
NO, IT'S WHAT WE WOULD HAVE
DONE AS SAVAII, ALSO.
ALTHOUGH, I DON'T THINK I WOULD
HAVE EATEN THE FOOT TODAY TO BE
HONEST.
I REALLY DID SEE THIS AS ONE
TRIBE SO THAT WAS HARD FOR ME TO
WATCH THEM EAT.
Jeff: BRANDON?
I LOVE YOU, DAWN, BUT YOU
TOLD US YOU WOULD WANT TO STAY
UP THERE AS LONG AS POSSIBLE SO
WE COULD EAT.
FOR SURE, FOR SURE.
YOU JUST CONTRADICTED WHAT
YOU SAID.
NO, I'M JUST SAYING IT WAS
HARD FOR ME.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
I DON'T BUY IT.
I MEAN, THAT'S WHY SAVAII TRIBE,
EXCLUDING COCHRAN, IS GOING TO
BE PICKED OFF JUST AS EXACTLY AS
THEY THINK THEY'RE GOING TO BE
PICKED OFF.
WE'RE TRYING TO BE NICE ABOUT
IT, BUT SOMETIMES IT JUST GETS
ON YOUR NERVES.
I'M NOT SURE I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU WERE SAYING THEY HAD
SAID.
I'M SORRY.
I THINK IT'S JUST A
MISCOMMUNICATION.
I DON'T THINK IT IS.
JUST LIKE SHE SAID THEY WOULD
HAVE DONE THE SAME THING WITH US
BUT IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A LOT
MORE RUTHLESS.
NO, BRANDON, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THEY'RE BEING NICE BECAUSE
THEY HAVE TO.
IT WAS LIKE I'M SO EXCITED THAT
YOU GUYS GOT TO EAT.
I WAS HAPPY YOU GOT TO.
DISMEN I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY
ATE.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
THAT DOESN'T ADD UP TO ME,
EITHER YOU ARE OKAY THAT WE
ATE-- DO YOU GET WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING.
BUT I WAS JUST SAYING IT WAS
HARD FOR ME.
THAT'S IT.
I'M SORRY.
LOOK AT MY.
BECAUSE I APOLOGIZE IF I'VE
OFFENDED YOU.
I FORGIVE YOU, I DO.
I MEAN IT.
I'VE BEEN GENUINE AND I REALLY
DO WANT TO GET TO KNOW YOU GITES
AND I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU'RE A
MAJORITY AND THAT'S THE WAY THE
GAME GOES.
I CAN PROMISE YOU, JEFF, NONE
OF US ARE GOING TO STOP UNTIL
THAT WHOLE SAVAII TRIBE IS
COMPLETELY...
Jeff: WHITNEY WHAT, DO YOU
MAKE OF ALL THIS, BECAUSE YOU'RE
SAFE TONIGHT BUT TOMORROW YOU
BECOME POTENTIALLY VULNERABLE
AGAIN.
OH, TOTALLY.
WILL FEEL LIKE WE DEFINITELY
HAVE BEEN VILIFIED BUT YET I
FEEL LIKE I'VE PLAYED THIS GAME
JUST AS HONESTLY AS THEY HAVE.
AND I GET WHAT DAWN WAS SAYING.
IT WAS JUST HARD BECAUSE WE'RE
HUNGRY, TOO, BUT WE HAVE TO
FIGHT FOR OUR LIVES, AND YOU ALL
DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
Jeff: WHAT HAS MADE YOU
EMOTIONAL?
SUDDENLY YOU'RE--
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN
COMPLETELY VILIFIED, AND THEY--
THEY DON'T EVEN ACCEPT AS, LIKE,
REAL PEOPLE.
WE WERE PAINTED AS BULLIES.
I NEVER ONCE WAS A BULLY.
IT'S HARD TO TAKE.
I'M NOT A BAD PERSON.
Jeff: BRANDON, IS IT HARD
FOR YOU TO SEE WHITNEY CRYING?
ABSOLUTELY.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE WHITNEY CRY.
I HAVE NOTHING PERSONAL AGAINST
ANYBODY BUT AT THE SAME TIME WE
WERE EXCLUDED UNTIL WE GOT
POWER.
THEN WE WERE THE VILLAINS.
I MEAN, I DON'T MEAN TO MAKE YOU
CRY, BUT IT'S-- IT'S-- IT'S A
NO-BRAINER FOR ME.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO THE VOTE.
WHITNEY, YOU HAVE IMMUNITY.
I DON'T HAVE TO ASK.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT GIVING IT UP.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
RICK, YOU'RE UP.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO
DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, EDNA.
EDNA.
TWO VOTES EDNA.
THREE VOTES EDNA.
JIM.
THREE VOTES EDNA, TWO VOTES JIM.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES EDNA, THREE VOTES
JIM.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JIM, THREE
VOTES EDNA.
JIM.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES JIM.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR:SOUTH PACIFIC," JIM.
THAT'S SIX.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JIM, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
A LOT WAS SAID TONIGHT, AND THE
BIG QUESTION IS WAS ANYTHING
REVEALED THAT MIGHT HELP DAWN OR
WHITNEY?
WE'LL FIND OUT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": ALBERT MAKES A BIG
MOVE.
MY ONLY REAL CHANCE TO WIN
THIS GAME IS TO SECURE EVERY
SAVAII VOTE.
Jeff: BUT COACH IS ON TO
HIM.
IF ANYBODY GOES AGAINST THE
FAMILY, THEY'RE DEAD.
Jeff: AT REDEMPTION ISLAND
OZZY LIES IN WAIT.
I'M HERE EATING THE BEST
PROTEIN POSSIBLE, EXERCISING
EVERY DAY, MAKING MYSELF
STRONGER.
WHAT'S UP, FELLAS?
THERE HE IS.
WHAT UP, DUDE?
I'M SAD.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I PLAYED A
GREAT GAME.
I THINK I POSITIONED MYSELF VERY
WELL FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS,
AND IT'S STILL A SHOT.
BUT IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE AS GOOD
OF A SHOT AS I HAD THREE DAYS
AGO.
I HATE TO SAY I TOLD YOU SO.
I THOUGHT WE WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THE FINAL THREE.