Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
SURVIVOR.
ON DAY 17 UPOLU AND THE
SAVAII TRIBE WERE DEAD EVEN.
SIX EACH.
UPOLU WINS.
SAVAII LOSES THE CHALLENGE
AND BLAMES COCHRAN.
WITH THE MERGE LOONLING OZZY
PROPOSES A RISKY PLAN.
I WOULD BE WILLING TO
SACRIFICE MYSELF, GO TO
REDEMPTION.
BEAT KRISTINE AND GET BACK IN
THE GAME AND GIVE OUR TRIBE AN
EDGE.
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I HAD A DREAM AND I SAW MY
CHANCE AT MY OWN REDEMPTION.
OZZY ALSO WANTED COCHRAN TO
BE A DOUBLE AGENT.
I WILL MAKE UP A STORY,
COCHRAN IS THE SMART WEASEL, HE
VOTE HIM OUT AND WHIPS OUT THE
IDOL, GOOD-BYE, OZZY.
AND GAVE OZZY HIS IMMUNITY
IDOL.
IN THE END, SAVAII WENT ALONG
WITH THE PLAN.
OZZY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW THE QUESTIONS ARE, CAN
OZZY WIN AT REDEMPTION ISLAND?
I AM OUT OF HERE?
WILL THERE BE A MERGE AND
CAN COCHRAN BE A MASTER SPY?
THE WEIRDEST MERGE IN SURVIVOR
HISTORY.
WHAT WHAT A DIFFERENCE THE
DAY MAKES.
A DAY AGO I THOUGHT I WAS
GOING TO REDEMPTION ISLAND,
WHERE I WOULD HUMILIATE MYSELF
AND GO HOME.
OZZY CAME FROM THE HEAVENS
AND GAVE THIS MIRACULOUS PLAN
WHERE HE WOULD SACRIFICE HIMSELF
ON THE BASIS OF THE TRIBE, BASED
ON THE MERGE THAT WILL TAKE
PLACE AND THE GAMBLE YOUR YOU
PROVE YOURSELF IN AN EXTREMELY
STRONG PLAYER AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
IF EVERYTHING CONNECTS IN THE
WAY WE HOPE IT WILL THIS IS
GOING TO GO DOWN IN HISTORY AS
ONE OF THE SINGLE BIGGEST AND
GREATEST MOVES IN SURVIVOR
HISTORY.
WHAT IS OUR BEST OPTION TO
STAY IN THE GAME?
I WAS WILLING TO GO.
YOU CAN EASILY SAY YOU ARE
WILLING TO GO, BUT TO ACTUALLY
DO IT, STEP UP AND TAKE CONTROL,
THAT IS DIFFERENT.
THE WAY I LIVE MY LIFE, I
DON'T LIVE IT FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
JUST STEP UP AND PROVE TO THE
WORLD WHAT YOU CAN DO.
WHAT CAN I DO IN TERMS OF OUR
PLAN IS.
I PRESUME IF I GO TO THE
OTHER SIDE THEY WILL ASK WHAT
BOND EXISTS BETWEEN ALL OF YOU.
YOU SAY WHAT YOU WANT, MAN.
YOU JUST HAVE TO --
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO SAY.
ANOTHER BIG PART OF THE PLAN
IS THAT I BECOME THE SORT OF
DOUBLE AGENT WHO WILL BE ABLE TO
FIGURE OUT WHO THE ZERO PO
THROUGH TRIBE PLANS TO VOTE OUT
IN THE EVENT OF A MERGE.
EVERYBODY IN THIS GAME IS
CAPABLE OF BEING A DOUBLE AGENT,
IF ANYBODY, IT IS ME.
I HAVE ALREADY BEEN
PRETENDING LIKE I LIKE THE
PEOPLE IN MY TRIBE AN 18-DAY, I
THINK I DESERVE AN ACADEMY AWARD
FOR THAT PERFORMANCE.
I WILL PLAY WHATEVER PART I
NEED TO PLAY.
I BET YOU NEVER THOUGHT THAT
WAS GOING TO HAPPEN.
NO.
THAT IS SWEET.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
RIGHT NOW, MY PHILOSOPHY, TO
TAKE FROM AL PACINO.
FIRST YOU GET THE EGO MANIA
PLAYER VOTED OUT AND THEN YOU
GET HIS IDOL AND THEN YOU GET
THE MILLION DOLLARS.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
HELLO, HELLO.
DID I WAKE YOU UP?
WHO IS IT?
THIS IS OZZY.
HI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
UNDER BETTER CIRCUMSTANCES.
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MAN.
IDOL.
WHAT?
YEAH.
WHO HAD IT?
GUESS.
COCHRAN.
YES.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
WELL, FROM LISTENING TO
PEOPLE.
OH!
THE LITTLE WEASEL.
I CAME INTO REDEMPTION AND I
PUT ON MY ACTOR SUIT.
AND ALL VOTED COCHRAN AND HE
PULLED OUT THE IDOL.
AND HE DIDN'T TELL ANYBODY?
NO.
I THINK SHE BOUGHT IT.
I THINK THAT SHE TOOK IT
HOOK, LINE AND SINKER.
I GET TAKEN OUT, I DIDN'T
PLAY THE IDOL THIS TIME AND --
LIKE WHAT IS IT WITH YOU
LAWYERS? ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
THIS IS PART OF THE PLAN.
FIRST STEP IS GETTING MYSELF
VOTED OUT.
THE SECOND STEP, GETTING HER TO
BELIEVE THAT, THIRD STEP,
BEATING HER AND GIVING THE OTHER
TRIBE FALSE INFORMATION.
THE MOVE IS PROBABLY EITHER
THE STUPIDEST THING I COULD HAVE
DONE OR THE CRAZIEST, BALLSIEST
THING I PROBABLY COULD EVER HAVE
THOUGHT OF DOING.
Jeff: NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUAL.
KRISTINE, THE BATTLE AGAINST
OZZY.
VOTED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
Jeff: WELCOME TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND ARENA, BOTH TRIBES ARE
HERE TO WITNESS TODAY'S DUAL.
OZZY, ARE YOU SURPRISED TO FIND
YOURSELF ON REDEMPTION ISLAND?
I MEAN, I GAVE PRETTY MUCH
EVERYTHING TO MY TRIBE, AND THEN
WE LOSE ONE CHALLENGE BECAUSE
SOMEBODY CAN'T OPERATE A CLIP,
AND THAT ENDS UP BEING THE
PERSON THAT SENDS ME HERE.
PLAYS THE IDOL, YOU DON'T EVEN
-- I KNOW SOMEONE ELSE PROBABLY
KNEW THAT YOU HAD IT, AS FAR AS
I AM CONCERNED, TRIBE
BOUNDARIES, I MEAN, AT THE
MERGE, THEY DON'T EXIST ANYMORE,
IT IS ALL ONE FOR ONE AND
WHOEVER STICKS TOGETHER FROM
THIS POINT ON MAKES IT THE
FURTHEST IN THE GAME.
BUT I THRIVE UNDER THE PRESSURE
TO COME BACK IN THE GAME FOR
REVENGE, BASICALLY.
ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S DUAL?
YEAH.
FOR TODAY'S DUAL YOU WILL USE
STICKS AND ROPES TO MAKE A LONG
POLE.
YOU WILL USE THE POLE TO
RETRIEVE THREE KEYS.
THE THREE KEYS OPEN THREE LOCKS.
THE FIRST PERSON TO SET THROUGH
THEIR DOOR WINS THIS DUAL.
THE LOSER IS OUT OF THE GAUGE
FOR GOOD.
THERE IS ONE SIGNIFICANT
DIFFERENCE WITH TODAY'S DUAL.
THE WINNER OF THIS DUAL DOES NOT
GO BACK TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THEY COME BACK INTO THE GAME.
HUGE SEX, ONE SHOT.
THIS IS IT.
PICK YOUR SPOTS.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ONE OF YOU WILL GET BACK IN THIS
GAME AND ONE OF YOU IS GOING
HOME.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS, READY.
GO.
YOUR FIRST GOAL IS TO BUILD
THAT POLE.
IT NEEDS TO BE LONG ENOUGH AND
STRONG ENOUGH TO REACH THE KEYS.
IF YOU PANIC AND MAKE A WEAK
ONE, IT WILL FALL APART AS SOON
AS YOU PUT IT THROUGH THE GATE.
KRISTINE IS GETTING MORE OUT OF
HER STICK, IT MAY TAKE FEWER
STICKS FOR KRISTINE.
TWO VERY DIFFERENT STRATEGIES.
KRISTINE GOING TO GIVE ATE
GO.
HOPING THAT HER POLE WILL BE
LONG ENOUGH AND STRONG ENOUGH TO
REACH A KEY.
KRISTINE'S POLE IS JUST LONG
ENOUGH.
BUT NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
OZZY IS GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
THIS IS WHERE THE STRATEGY OF
HOW YOU TIE YOUR STICKS TOGETHER
WILL PAY OFF OR WORK AGAINST
YOU.
KRISTINE VERY CLOSE.
KRISTINE'S POLE IS JUST SHORT.
OZZY, HE HAS THE POLE ON HIS KEY
RING, IS IT STRONG MUST HAVE TO
GET IT ALL THE WAY BACK? IT IS
HANGING ON BY THE EDGE OF THE
POLE.
AND IT DROPS.
KRISTINE'S POLE IS STARTING TO
FALL APART, SHE HAS TO TAKE IT
BACK FOR MORE REPAIRS.
OZZY ALMOST THERE.
CAN HE HOOK IT? AND HE DOES.
OZZY HAS HIS KEY AGAIN.
THIS TIME IT IS STAYING ON.
OZZY HAS HIS FIRST KEY.
LOOKING FOR TWO MORE.
KRISTINE, QUICKLY MAKING AN
ADJUSTMENT.
OZZY STRETCHING OUT AGAIN HIS
POLE, JUST LONG ENOUGH.
OZZY HAS THE SECOND KEY.
OZZY NOW WITH ONE KEY LEFT,
KRISTINE NEEDS TO PICK IT UP
RIGHT NOW.
OZZY HAS HIS THIRD KEY! OZZY
HAS ALL THREE KEYS.
KRISTINE HAS NONE.
OZZY NOW HAS TO UNLOCK THE LOCKS
AND THIS DUAL IS OVER.
OZZY HAS ONE LOCK UNDONE.
KRISTINE NOT GIVING UP WITH THAT
POLE, THAT POLE IS FALLING
APART.
OZZY HAS HIS SECOND LOCK UNDONE.
THIS WILL DO IT.
OZZY UNLOCKS THE THIRD LOCK.
OZZY WINS THE DUAL AND IS BACK
IN THIS GAME!
GREAT GAME!
Jeff: KRISTINE, AFTER 19
DIFFICULT DAYS YOUR ADVENTURE
HAS COME TO AN END.
IT IS.
IT IS A GOOD 40TH BIRTHDAY
PRESENT.
IT IS TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD LUCK.
WAY TO GO KRISTINE.
GOOD LUCK, EVERYBODY.
THIS MIGHT EXPLODE, CAREFUL.
STAY BACK.
Jeff: OZZY AS FAST AS YOU
WERE OUT OF THIS GAME YOU ARE
BACK IN THIS GAME.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU ARE NOW BACK IN THE HUNT FOR
THE MONEY, AND YOU AND EVERYBODY
ELSE HERE CAN DROP YOUR BUFFS.
YES!
Jeff: BECAUSE WE ARE
MERGED.
COCHRAN. ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
YOU CAN HEAD BACK.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
I JUST MADE THE CRAZIEST MOVE
YOU COULD POSSIBLY MAKE AND NOW
I CAN ONLY HOPE THAT COCHRAN IS
GOING TO BE ABLE TO INFILTRATE
UPOLU AND TAKE THE ADVANTAGE,
TAKE THE LEAD AND TAKE US TO
VICTORY.
WELCOME!
WHERE ARE YOU FROM? HOUSTON.
WHERE ARE YOU FROM? I WAS
BORN IN KNOXVILLE.
WE MERGED TRIBES.
EVERYBODY DOES THEIR HANDS
SHAKES AND HAVE A NICE LITTLE
MEAL.
IMMEDIATELY IT IS GAME ON,
THOUGH.
IT IS SIX ON SIX.
SO EVERYBODY IS LOOKING FOR AN
EDGE.
LAST NIGHT?
IT IS LIKE A REBIRTH.
I WOKE UP, AND IT IS LIKE -- IT
IS TRUE.
THIS IS WHERE THE REAL GAME
BEGINS RIGHT NOW.
OUR PLAN WORKED PERFECTLY,
OZZY, THERE WAS A MERGE, WE ARE
BACK TO SIX AND NOW IT IS TIME
FOR ME TO WORK MY MAGIC LIKE I
KNEW A I COULD ALL ALONG AND BE
THE DOUBLE AGENT,.
THE WAY THEY TREATED ME, I
THOUGHT IT WAS HORRIBLE.
LIKE KEITH, THE WAY KEITH
TALKED TO ME, I FELT OSTRACIZED.
I MEAN THEY HATED ME BEFORE
--
STRATEGICALLY, I AM
WONDERING, IF I AM WORKING WITH
THE RIGHT PEOPLE RIGHT NOW.
HERE IS THE THING.
I AM GOING TO TELL YOU RIGHT
NOW.
OUR TRIBE -- I FEEL LIKE YOU
GUYS ARE TRYING TO PLAY US.
OKAY? YOU GUYS CAME UP WITH A
STORY, YOU GUYS SENT HIM TO
REDEMPTION, YOU HAVE AN IDOL IN
YOUR POCKET, AND KNOWING THAT
OZZY WOULD WIN REDEMPTION, IT
WAS A RISK, THAT OZZY WOULD WIN
REDEMPTION.
OKAY?
OKAY.
WE WILL VOTE SIX STRONG, AND
IF ALL SIX SURVIVOR AND VOTE
TOGETHER THERE IS A ONE IN FIVE
CHANCE YOU ARE GOING TO DRAW A
BLACK ROCK.
AND SO WILL I.
THAT'S THE WAY TO PLAY THE GAME.
YEAH.
I WILL TELL YOU, WHETHER OR
NOT THESE PEOPLE HAVE REALLY
TREATED YOU LIKE THAT, I AM JUST
SAYING, WHETHER THEY HAVE OR
NOT, LET'S SAY THEY TREATED YOU
LIKE GOLD, I KNOW, THAT'S WHAT I
AM SAYING, I KNOW WHAT THOSE
KIND OF PEOPLE THINK.
I HAVE BEEN MADE FUN OF MY
WHOLE LIFE, OKAY? I MIGHT BE
THE DRAGON SLAYER NOW, BUT I
KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE TO BE
SUPERIOR IN ONE WAY TO PEOPLE
AND THEY KNOW IT, SO THEY FIND
WAYS THAT YOU ARE INFERIOR TO
THEM.
I KNOW WHAT THAT FEELS LIKE,
MAN, BUT YOU HAVE A CHANCE TO
CHANGE THE GAME FOR YOURSELF.
THERE IS A LINE IN THE SAND.
COME ACROSS THAT LINE.
ALL IN ALL, WHAT I TOOK AWAY
FROM COACH IS HE IS INCREDIBLY
INTELLIGENT GUY.
I WATCHED HIM, HE IS
ECCENTRIC, DRAGON SLAYER WHO
TALKS ABOUT BUSINESS SARDZ AND
KING ARTHUR, BUT HE IS A SMART
GUY AND COACH LAID IT ALL ON THE
TABLE FOR ME SAYING, I COULD
MAKE US DRAW ROCKS THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL OR WHAT I AM
SERIOUSLY CONSIDERING I COULD
COMPLETELY JUMP SHIP AND BETRAY
MY OLD TRIBE AND JOIN UPOLU.
THERE WAS NO ILLUSION.
I SAW SOME OF THOSE PEOPLE IN
TEARS.
THE NIGHT OF THE CHALLENGE --
I MEAN --
OZZY WOKE UP, HE HAD A DREAM.
THE DREAM WAS HE WANTS
REDEMPTION.
IT IS NOT DISLOYAL --
THE WRITING ON THE WALL IS
THAT YOU ARE NOT IN THEIR,
WHATEVER, INNER CIRCLE FOR
WHATEVER REASON.
YOU HAVE BEEN MISTREATED LIKE
YOU MADE IT PRETTY CLEARLY
OBVIOUS.
I THINK PART OF THE IDEA
RIGHT NOW IS I AM SUPPOSED TO BE
GATHERING INFORMATION, YOU KNOW.
OH, IS THAT WHAT THEY HAVE
COMMANDED?
YEAH.
WHO HAS BEEN GIVING YOU THE
MOST TROUBLE AND WHO WOULD GIVE
YOU THE MOST SCARED --
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
KEITH HAS BEEN MORE
CONSISTENTLY WITH ME
BY ALL MEANS YOU WILL BE
COMPLETELY PROTECTED BY ME FROM
ANY OF THEM.
THERE IS A LOT OF DOWN SIDES
TO JUMPING SHIP, BUT ON THE
OTHER HAND, I DO BELIEVE THE
UPOLU MEMBERS ARE SUPER SOLID,
COMPLETELY HONEST, AND
TRUSTWORTHY, YOU KNOW, I
CONSIDER MYSELF A STRATEGY GIST,
AND MAYBE EVEN A MASTERMIND BUT
NOT AN EVIL MASTERMIND, SO I
RETURN TO GIVE THE IMMUNITY IDOL
TO OZZY, HE GAVE IT TO ME IN
COMPLETE TRUST AND I AM GOING TO
RECIPROCATE, UP TO THE POINT IN
THE GAME I FEEL LIKE I HAVE BEEN
PUTTING MY FATE IN THE HANDS OF
TRIBE MATE I DON'T ENTIRELY
TRUST AND WHO, A AND WHO DON'T
ENTIRELY RESPECT ME, NOW IT HAS
BECOME AN INDIVIDUAL GAME AND I
FEEL LIKE I AM IN CONTROL OF MY
FATE.
I HAVE DECISIONS OF WHO I WANT
TO WORK WITH AND BETRAY.
IT IS A LITTLE SURREAL BUT ALSO
A LITTLE BIT OF EXCITING THAT I
AM THE PERSON RIGHT NOW THAT
GETS TO DECIDE HOW SURVIVOR
SOUTH PACIFIC TAKES SHAPE AND
POSSIBLY ENDS.
WHAT IS YOUR PLAN?
I AM VOTE STRAIGHT TICKET
REGARDLESS.
IF THERE IS A TIE, THERE IS A
REVOTE, I JUST WANT TO DRAW A
ROCK.
I DO FEEL LIKE THERE HAS BEEN
A TON OF DISRESPECT, AND A
FLASHBACK THE LAST 21 DAYS WE
ARE ON THE OUTS.
COCHRAN AND I WENT TO GET
TREE MAIL THIS MORNING AND I
KNOW FOR PROBABLY A GOOD 20 DAYS
THAT COCHRAN AND I HAVE BEEN OUT
HERE I WATCHED COCHRAN
SPECIFICALLY BE REALLY TREATED
NOT AS AN EQUAL IN THE GROUP.
THAT'S WHAT I HAVE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT RECENTLY.
OH, GOSH.
I AM CRYING AT TREE MAIL.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT?
I FEEL LIKE WE AGREED TO STAY
WITH EVERYBODY ON THE TRIBE AND
I JUST FEEL LIKE YOU MEET THESE
PEOPLE AND THEY ARE A LOT -- IT
IS FRUSTRATING.
DON'T WORRY.
AS A SURVIVOR FAN AND I WATCH
THE GAME I LOVE TO WATCH PEOPLE
STAND UP FOR WHAT THEY BELIEVE
IN, KIND OF AT THE EXPENSE OF
THE MILLION DOLLARS.
I MEAN I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD
HAVE STOOD UP FOR COCHRAN
SOONER.
SORRY.
HE IS A REALLY GREAT KID, AND HE
REMINDS ME A LOT OF, I HAVE A
SON THAT REMINDS ME ON OF HIM,
WITH RED HAIR BUT YOU TRY TO
PROTECT YOUR INTERESTS AND YOU
WANT TO STAY.
WHAT I HAVE BEEN THINKING IS,
UP UNTIL THIS POINT, MY ENTIRE
STATE IN THE GAME, FATE IN THE
GAME HAS BEEN HANDED OVER TO
OTHER PEOPLE, BUT I HAVE BEEN
GROVELING AND BEGGING NOT TO BE
VOTED OUT SINCE THE FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, NOW WHAT WE ARE
EXPECTING TO DO, EXPECTED TO DO
IS COMPLETELY GIVE OF OUR GAMES,
WITH THE WHOLE DRAWING ROCK
THING, FROM THE FIRST MOMENT
WHEN I AND I THINK YOU TOO CAN
FINALLY DECIDE ON WHAT COURSE TO
TAKE.
OKAY.
AND I ALWAYS TRIED TO
REMEMBER IT IS A GAME FOR A
MILLION DOLLARS, YOU KNOW, AND
THAT THIS IS A GAME WITH
CASUALTIES, BUT I DON'T REALLY
WANT THE CASUALTY TO BE COCHRAN.
YES, IT IS FRIGHTENING HOW
ALLIANCES SWING.
IT IS MORE THAN PARANOID
AGGRAVATION.
YOU ARE COLD AND TIRED AND
LOSING SLEEP ONLY THE NECKLACE
GIVES A SAFE SENSATION.
OKAY.
GAME ON.
AND IN SOME WAYS, THIS IS A
WAY FOR ME TO SAY I DON'T LIKE
THE WAY IT HAS BEEN GOING, EVEN
IF IT MEANS, YOU KNOW, I LOSE MY
FOOTING IN THE GAME.
COME ON IN, GUYS.
SO, KEITH, WHAT IS THE NEW
TRIBE NAME?
THE NEW TRIBE NAME IS BASED
FROM THE STORY OF HOW THE
COCONUT GAME TO ME, TETUNA.
YOU ARE READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AND I WILL TAKE BACK
TRIBAL IMMUNITY.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NO MORE,
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IS NOW WHAT
YOU COVET.
TODAY, THERE ARE TWO NECKLACES,
BECAUSE TWO PEOPLE WILL LEAVE
THIS CHALLENGE WITH IMMUNITY,
ONE MAN AND ONE WOMAN.
HERE IS HOW IT WORKS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
BALANCE ON A SMALL PERCH WHILE
HOLDING A COCONUT BETWEEN TWO
ROPES, AT REGULAR INTERVALS WE
WILL ADD MORE ROPE MAKING IT
MORE DIFFICULT TO HOLD ON TO THE
COCONUT.
IF AT ANY POINT YOUR COCONUT
DROPS, OR YOU STEP OFF THE PER.
, YOU ARE OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
LAST MAN, LAST WOMAN STANDING,
WINS IMMUNITY AND ARE SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE WILL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO, SIX
FORMER SAVAII AND SIX FORMER
UPOLU.
MAKE SURE YOUR FEET ARE
COMFORTABLE.
EVERYBODY SLIDE YOUR ROPE OVER
THE COCONUT.
PICK IT UP.
HOLD THOSE ROPES TAUGHT,
REMEMBER, IT CAN'T BE AGAINST
YOUR BODY.
COCHRAN IS ALREADY WAVERING.
THE KEY TO THIS IS JUST KEEPING
BALANCE, WHICH MEANS YOU HAVE TO
STAY CONCENTRATING ALL THE TIME,
IT IS HARD TO DO AFTER 21 DAYS
IN THIS GAME.
EDNA, UP AGAINST THE BODY AND
EDNA IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
COCHRAN FALLS OFF SECONDS
BEHIND.
THE FIRST WOMAN AND THE FIRST
MAN ARE OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
HANG IN THERE.
KEEP CONCENTRATING.
THREE, TWO, 1.
THIS ROUND IS OVER.
YOU ARE SAFE.
HERE WE GO, EVERYBODY PUT YOUR
ROPE OVER YOUR COKE PUT FOR THE
SECOND ROUND.
ROPES ARE NOW LONGER, IT WILL BE
MORE DIFFICULT.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
PICK UP YOUR COCONUT.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
SAME RULES APPLY.
WHITNEY IS OUT RIGHT AWAY.
YOU ARE DOWN TO TWO WOMEN VYING
FOR IMMUNITY TONIGHT.
SOPHIE'S, LEGS SHAKING BUT STILL
DOING A GOOD JOB.
AND WITH THAT, SOPHIE DROPS OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
DAWN WINS IMMUNITY FOR THE
WOMEN.
THE MEN STILL VYING FOR
IMMUNITY.
RICK, BRANDON, OZZY, JIM,
ALBERT, KEITH, AND COACH.
COACH DROPS HIS COCONUT,
COACH IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO SIX GUYS
LEFT.
RICK WAS WOBBLING AT THE END OF
THE FIRST ROUND AND HE IS STILL
WOBBLING.
THAT IS THE COWBOY STRENGTH
HOLDING ON THERE.
RICK CAN HANG ON NO LONGER.
RICK IS NOW OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
15 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
HANG ON.
AND YOU WILL MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND.
JIM DROPS OUT AND KEITH DROPS
OUT RIGHT BEHIND HIM, WE ARE
DOWN TO THREE.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
YOU ARE SAFE.
NICE JOB.
YOU ARE DOWN TO BRANDON, OZZY,
AND ALBERT.
WE WILL GO NOW UNTIL WE HAVE A
WINNER.
WE HAVE EXTENDED THE ROPE AS FAR
AS IT WILL GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE, LIFT.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
THIS IS GOING TO BE DIFFICULT.
IT IS ONE OF THE HOTTEST DAYS WE
HAVE HAD OUT HERE.
BRANDON, READJUSTS.
BRANDON IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
ONE FORMER SAVAII, ONE FORMER
UPOLU, NOW IT IS JUST ENDURANCE.
ALBERT LOOKING STRONG.
OZZY HAS GOT A BIT OF A WOBBLE.
SWEAT POURING OFFER BOTH GUYS.
STILL FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
HANG IN THERE.
ALBERT DROPS OUT, OZZY WINS
IMMUNITY, AND DAWN WINS IMMUNITY
FOR THE WOMEN.
DAWN, COME ON OVER.
RUNNING OVER HERE.
OZZY, COME ON OVER.
DAWN AND OZZY, SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL, AS FOR
THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 21 DAYS
ONE OF YOU WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT IS GOING TO BE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND SEE YOU BACK
AT CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU BACK AT TRIBAL.
GREAT JOB.
HEY, YOU GUYS DID WHAT WE NEEDED
TO DO, SERIOUSLY.
INCREASE THE NUMBERS, BIG TIME.
FOUR TO SIX NOW.
WE BETTER START REEVALUATING
WHERE THEY ALL LIE.
SOPHIE WOULD BE MY PICK.
IF ANYTHING IF WE ARE GOING
TO SWING ANY OTHER WAY IT IS FOR
RICK.
I THINK WE RUN THE LEAST
AMOUNT OF RISK IN TERMS OF AN
IDOL PLAY IF WE GO WITH RICK.
ONE MORE TIME.
EVERYBODY IS SOLID?
YES.
WE ARE ALL THROWING ROCKS.
PHYSICALLY.
OKAY, NOW I AM WORRIED.
EVERYBODY IS OKAY WITH
THROWING ROCKS.
KEITH, ARE YOU THROWING A ROCK?
YEAH.
AS OF RIGHT NOW, MY
IMPRESSION IS THAT BOTH TRIBES
BELIEVE THAT IT IS GOING TO BE A
DEADLOCK AT THE VOTE.
NOBODY LIKES THE IDEA OF PICKING
ROCKS FOR A MILLION DOLLARS.
BUT GO SAVAII MEMBERS HAVE
IMMUNITY, IT IS GREAT FOR US
BECAUSE IF IT COMES DOWN TO A
PICK EM THERE ARE TEN PICKS AND
ONLY FOUR OF US ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK AND SIX OF THEM.
SO YOU AND I ARE OUT OF THE
VOTE.
WE ARE OUT OF THE VOTE AND
WHOEVER PLAYS THE IDOL IS OUT OF
THE VOTE.
THEY WOULD NEVER THINK THAT
WHITNEY WOULD HAVE IT.
NOT EVER.
WHICH MEANS I PRETTY MUCH
BASICALLY HAVE TO PLAY THE IDOL.
I THINK THEY ARE GOING TO
VOTE FOR WHITNEY.
WHY? BECAUSE IF IT GOES TO
ROCKS, WHITNEY IS IMMUNE FROM
THE ROCKS AND THEY WANT TO HAVE
SOME OF THE STRONGER PLAYERS IN
THERE, ME AND KEITH, AND IN
THEIR MINDS, THEY CAN GET RID OF
WHITNEY LATER.
DO WE WANT TO HAVE COCHRAN,
THEN, STILL BE A LITTLE WAFFLY
TODAY?
IF THEY TELL ME MIGHT BE TO
VOTE FOR THEN WE KNOW THAT'S NOT
WHO THEY ARE VOTING FOR.
SAVAII MAY FEEL CONFIDENT
THAT WE HAVE A THREE OUT OF
EIGHT SHOT OR WHATEVER THE
NUMBERS ARE, BUT THOSE NUMBERS
AREN'T THAT REASSURING TO ME,
EVEN IF IT IS ONE OUT OF 30 THAT
A ROCK WOULD SEND ME HOME I
WOULDN'T WANT TO DO IT.
THAT IS NOT WHAT THIS GAME IS
ABOUT.
I LOVE THIS GAME AND RESPECT
THIS GAME BUT I DON'T RESPECT
REDUCING MY GAME TO A GAME OF
CHANCE AND PULLING A ROCK OUT OF
A BAG.
WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN IS,
THEY ARE GOING TO VOTE FOR RICK.
ORIGINALLY IT WAS GOING TO BE
YOU.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE
ME.
THE LAST SECOND, OZZY IS
GOING TO STAND UP, GIVE -- I
MEAN, HAVE LIKE RICK PLAY IDOL
AND --
RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND, BUT I THINK THAT
THIS IS SURVIVOR.
I TRUST YOU.
BUT HAVE GOT TO REALIZE WHERE WE
ARE KOCHING FROM.
I DO, I DO.
I HOPE -- DON'T DO ME ANY
FAVORS.
DON'T LET ME GET EATEN ALIVE.
I KNOW IT IS GOING TO BE --
YEAH, IT IS NOT GOING TO BE
FUN.
YOU CAN NEVER COUNT ON
SOMEONE COMING OVER AND NEVER
KNOW FOR SURE.
THAT SAID, I THINK I FEEL AS
CONFIDENT ABOUT COCHRAN FLING
OVER, BECAUSE COCHRAN THINKS IF
HE PUSHES AND COMES BACK TO CAMP
HE IS GOING TO GET BEAT UP,
WHICH IS A LEGITIMATE THING FOR
A TARGET TO BE AFRAID OF.
THEY ARE GOING TO KILL ME
TONIGHT.
THEY ARE GOING TO EAT ME ALIVE.
THAT IS WHAT I AM DREADING.
I THINK YOU ARE GOING TO EAT
THEM ALIVE.
WHERE AM I SLEEPING TONIGHT?
RIGHT BETWEEN ME AND EDNA.
WHEREVER YOU WANT.
CARTE BLANCHE.
WE REALLY DON'T HAVE ANY
TWISTS BUT TO FLUS COCHRAN
BECAUSE THE ODDS ARE NOT IN OUR
FAVOR, IT LOOKS GRIM, IT LOOKS
DISMAL, SO I HAVE DONE
EVERYTHING I COULD, I HAVE
GOTTEN COCHRAN ON OUR SIDE TO
PLAY THE REST OF THIS GAME, I
HAVE CONVINCED HIM HE WILL BE
VALUED OVER HERE AND I HAVE
CONVINCED COCHRAN HE WILL BE THE
MAN OF THE MATCH, THE WEAK WILL
FINALLY BECOME STRONG, THAT THE
NERD WILL FINALLY RISE UP TO THE
BULLY AND GIVE HIM A BULLY
BEATDOWN.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
OH, I AM -- I WON'T SAY A
THING.
I AM JUST GOING TO LET YOU PLAY.
THAT IS MY PRELIMINARY PLAN.
I MEAN THERE ARE A FEW OUTS.
BEFORE THE CHALLENGE, I JUST
THOUGHT, TO ME, THIS IS LIKE
STARTING A WAR AND THAT IS NOT
HOW YOU REMEDY SOMETHING.
I CAN'T MAKE ANY PROMISES.
THEY ARE PROMISES, THOUGH.
WHY WOULD THEY WATCH OUT FOR
YOU OVER THEIR OWN PEOPLE.
IF THEY HAVE TWO OF THEIR
PEOPLE WINNING IMMUNITY TODAY
THEY WOULDN'T BE TALKING TO YOU.
DAWN APPARENTLY IS NOW
UNWILLING TO FLIP HER VOTE
ALONGSIDE ME AND UPOLU, IT GIVES
ME SOME PAUSE IN DEBATING
WHETHER OR NOT I WANT TO MAKE
THE JUMP, BUT IT IS A TOUGH
CHOICE, SHOULD GUY WITH A BUNCH
OF PEOPLE WHO HAVE KIND OF BEEN
RUDE TO ME PAST 21 DAYS OR DITCH
THE ENTIRE ROCK SCENARIO AND
COST MYSELF A MILLION DOLLARS
BECAUSE I WILL CAUSE SO MANY
PEOPLE TO BE FURIOUS AT ME.
I TOTALLY WILL PLAY YOUR GAME
I AM TELLING YOU WHAT GOES
AROUND COPS AROUND, THE WAY YOU
TREAT PEOPLE, TOTALLY AFFECTS
THE WAY THAT YOU LIVE YOUR LIFE,
AND I THINK THAT IS GOING TO
AFFECT EVERYTHING.
THERE IS NO WAY THAT --
THE RUDENESS, THE LACK OF
COURTESY, THE LACK OF RESPECT --
I WANT TO BE IN CONTROL FOR
THE FIRST TIME IN MY GAME.
I FEEL LIKE I AM BY SAYING
YOU KNOW WHAT? I WON'T TAKE
YOUR CRAP.
LOOK, IT IS NOT ABOUT THAT AT
THIS POINT.
IT IS ABOUT THAT.
TO ME, YOU ARE APPEALING TO YOUR
EMOTION.
I AM AN EMOTIONAL GUY.
OH, BEFORE I WENT TO THE
CHALLENGE, I REALLY SPENT SOME
TIME LIKE LITERALLY PRAYING, I
KNOW IT SOUNDS CLICHE BUT I KIND
OF BACKED OFF MY ORIGINAL
FEELING OF MAYBE I SHOULD FLIP
WITH COCHRAN, BECAUSE I REALIZED
I HAVE LIKED MY TRIBE, IT HASN'T
BEEN AS KUMBAYA AS I THINK THE
OTHER TRIBE BUT THERE ARE THINGS
ABOUT EACH OF THOSE PEOPLE I
LOVE AND I HAVE HAD GREAT
EXPERIENCES WITH THEM AND I
DON'T WANT TO GO BACK ON THAT, I
WANT TO STAY LOYAL TO THE TRIBE.
HOW ARE YOU DOING, BRO?
WE ARE ALMOST THERE.
GET BACK IN THE FOLD.
I HAVEN'T TALKED TO THE REST
OF THE TRIBE BECAUSE I CAN
UNDERSTAND WHY HE IS BEHALFING
BUT I AM PRAYING HE DOESN'T AND
I HAVE LET HIM KNOW I AM
DISAPPOINTED, I DON'T THINK IT
IS RIGHT TO PHLEGM, I DON'T.
AND I FEEL LIKE HE IS WATCHING
OUT FOR HIMSELF TONIGHT AND NO
ONE ELSE, BUT I DON'T WANT TO
TELL EVERYBODY, BECAUSE I THINK
THERE IS HOPE THAT HE IS GOING
TO NOT DO DO IT, I HAVE LET HIM
KNOW, I DON'T WANT YOU TO DO IT.
SO, COACH, SIX FORMER SAVAII,
SIX FORMER UPOLU, IF YOU WERE
GOING TO MAKE AN ASSUMPTION IT
SEEMS THAT WE MIGHT BE LOOKING
AT A TIE VOTE TONIGHT.
THAT IS CORRECT WE WILL BE
PUTTING ALL OF THE CARDS ON
TABLE TONIGHT.
AND YOU WILL SEE MOST LIKELY SIX
AND SIX.
Jeff: OZZY, RING TRUE TO
YOU?
YEAH.
DEFINITELY.
WE WENT INTO THIS CHALLENGE
TODAY KNOWING WE REALLY NEEDED
TO GET BOTH OF THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACES BECAUSE CHANCES WERE
WE ARE GOING TO TIE UP AND IT
WAS GOING TO GO TO ROCKS AND IF
IT DOES, WE BETTER HAVE THE ODDS
ON OUR SIDE, AND WE ARE ALL
GOING TO BE SAFE, I GUESS.
Jeff: AND THE REASON THE
STAKES ARE SO HIGH, DAWN,
BECAUSE IF YOU GO TO A TIE AND
WE VOTE AGAIN AND YOU ARE STILL
TIED THE TWO PEOPLE WHO HAVE
VOTES ARE IMMUNE AND EVERYBODY
ELSE IS DRAWING ROCKS WHICH IS A
BIG RISK.
BIG SEX.
IT IS WORTH A BIG RISK.
SO THE ONLY WAY TO BREAK UP A
TIE IS SOMEBODY HAS TO DEFECT TO
THE OTHER TRIBE.
EDNA, CAN YOU SEE ANY SCENARIO
THAT MIGHT MAKE SENSE FOR
SOMEBODY TO SWITCH?
IF THAT ONE INDIVIDUAL DIDN'T
FEEL INCORPORATED OR A PART OF
THAT TRIBE, THAT WOULD BE ONE
REASON.
Jeff: COCHRAN YOU HAVE SAID
IT MANY TIMES YOU ARE A STUDENT
OF THE GAME.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS THAT YOU WOULD
HAVE TWO TRIBES THIS UNIFIED?
I HAVE NEVER SEEN TWO TRIBES
THAT SEEM SO ENTIRELY COHESIVE
IN THEIR OWN SEPARATE WAYS, IN
TERMS OF ODDS, I DON'T KNOW
ODDS, I DON'T DO ODDS, I DO
SURVIVOR.
Jeff: JIM, WHAT ARE THE
CHANCES SOMEBODY FROM YOUR TRIBE
WALKS OVER AND JOINS THEIR
TRIBE?
ZERO, IT MAKES NO SENSE WE
HAVE THE NUMBERS ON OUR SIDE, IT
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE FOR ONE
OF US TO DO THAT.
Jeff: ALBERT IS THERE MUCH
TALK ABOUT THE IDOL, WHETHER
EACH TRIBE MAY HAVE FOUND AN
IDOL.
WE WERE ALL PRESENT AT THE
DUAL AND OZZY DID HIS BEST
BROADWAY PRODUCTION TO SEE HOW
HE FELT BACK STAB AND HURT ABOUT
THE IDOL AND TIME TO FIND OUT IF
THAT WAS ALL A SHOW, BECAUSE IF
THEY HAVE AN IDOL THAT THEY
PLAY, THAT MEANS THERE WASN'T
REALLY AN IDOL PLAYED AT THEIR
ORIGINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
Jeff: SOPHIE, IS IT A
CONSENSUS OZZY WASN'T TELLING
THE TRUTH OR IS IT A QUESTION
AND YOU ARE HOPING TO FIND OUT
TONIGHT?
I WAS ACTUALLY OFFENDED AT
REDEMPTION KIND THE SIX OF THEM
THOUGHT WE WOULD BELIEVE THAT
AND I FOUND IT TO BE OVER THE
TOP AND SOMEWHAT PATHETIC.
Jeff: OZZY?
YEAH, IT WAS A PERFORMANCE,
MAYBE IT WAS A LITTLE
LACKLUSTER, MAYBE TOO OVER THE
TOP AND YOU GUYS ARE RIGHT, I DO
HAVE THE IDOL.
OR RATHER, WE DO HAVE THE IDOL.
AND THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS, I
WAS JUST TRYING TO FIGHT FOR MY
TRIBE AND GIVE US SOME SORT OF
AN ADVANTAGE, AND IF THAT WAS
PATHETIC, THEN SO BE IT.
Jeff: AND YOU WERE VERY
CLEAR JUST THEN, OZZY ABOUT
SAYING, WE HAVE THE IDOL.
YES.
DEFINITELY FOR THIS GROUP.
AND MOST LIKELY THIS VOTE.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO TAKE MY
WORD FOR IT, WE CAN GO AHEAD AND
DO THIS.
THAT'S IT.
Jeff: WITH THAT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR OZZY.
YOU CAN'T VOTE FOR DAWN.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
RICK.
YOU ARE UP.
Jeff: I WILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW IS THE TIME
TO DO SO.
I WILL PLAY IT.
MIGHT AS WELL. IHFE GOT IT.
I HAVE GOT IT.
FOR WHITNEY.
Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR WHITNEY WILL
NOT COUNT.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KEITH.
KEITH.
FOUR VOTES, KEITH.
THAT IS FIVE VOTES, KEITH.
KEITH.
SIX VOTES KEITH.
RICK.
, RICK.
THREE FOR RICK.
COWBOY, RICK.
RICK.
THAT IS FIVE VOTES, RICK, SIX
VOTES APIECE.
RICK.
WE ARE TIED.
HERE IS WHAT WE ARE GOING TO DO.
WE ARE GOING TO REVOTE.
YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR KEITH OR
RICK.
KEITH AND RICK YOU WILL NOT
VOTE.
IF ANYBODY IS THINKING ABOUT
CHANGING THEIR VOTE, THIS IS
YOUR LAST CHANCE.
EDNA, GO GRAB THE URN AND YOU
CAN VOTE.
Jeff: I WILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I WILL GO READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KEITH.
KEITH, TWO VOTES KEITH.
THAT IS THREE VOTES KEITH.
KEITH.
FOUR VOTES KEITH.
FIVE VOTES KEITH.
RICK, RICK.
TWO VOTES RICK.
RICK.
THREE VOTES RICK.
FOUR VOTES RICK.
FIVE VOTES KEITH.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
KEITH.
YOU NEED TO BRING YOUR TORCH.
KEITH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME, GRAB YOUR
TORCH AND HEAD TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
COWARD.
DON'T TALK TO HIM LIKE THAT.
THAT'S WHAT HE IS.
WELL, THAT WAS WITHOUT QUESTION
THE BIGGEST MOVE IN THE GAME
THUS FAR.
AND THIS GAME IS FAR FROM OVER.
GRAB YOUR TORCH AND HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR.
YOU TOTALLY SCREWED ME OVER.
YOU DISGUST ME.
MY HOPE I CAN GET A COUPLE TO
VOTE FOR COCHRAN.
HE IS TALKING ABOUT THE GAME.
HE KNOWS WHAT WILL HAPPEN IN
THIS GAME.
I WILL NEVER GIVE UP.
OZZY, THERE IS NO WAY THAT HE
WOULD HAVE FLIPPED, BECAUSE I
DON'T KNOW WHY HE WOULD HAVE
WASTED THE IDOL, SO REALLY, IT
ONLY LEAVES ONE LITTLE WEASEL
LEFT, COCHRAN BACK STABBED US
ALL
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by Media Access Group
at WGBH. access.wgbh.org