Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
AT UPOLU, COACH THOUGHT HE
HAD ASSEMBLED A SOLID ALLIANCE
OF FIVE.
RICK, SOPHIE, BRANDON, AND
ALBERT.
Jeff: AND TACKED ON EDNA AS
A SPARE SIXTH WHILE LEAVING
STATEY AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
PECKING ORDER.
I DO BELIEVE THEY ARE LOOKING
TO TRY TO GET RID OF ME.
Jeff: BUT BRANDON STARTED
BEHAVING ERRATICALLY.
MY NAME IS BRANDON HANTZ.
I'M RUSSELL HANTZ'S NEPHEW.
Jeff: HE COVERTLY TARGETED
MIKAYLA.
MIKAYLA WILL BE GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
Jeff: LATER ME BLEW UP IN
FRONT OF THE ENTIRE TRIBE.
I WAS VERY UPSET.
HERE'S EVIL, PERIOD.
Jeff: BRANDON'S LOOSE
CANNON BEHAVIOR PUT EVERYONE ON
EDGE, ESPECIALLY COACH.
BRANDON JUST WORRIES ME.
YOU'RE ROYAL OR YOU'RE DISLOYAL.
Jeff: AT SAVAII, OZZY WAS
ALSO IN AN ALLIANCE OF FIVE AND
HE THOUGHT HE WAS IN CHARGE.
LIFE IS GOOD RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: THEY LEFT THE OLDEST
AND NERDIEST ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK.
I HAVE THIS REPUTATION AS THE
NERVOUS, NEUROTIC SCRAMBLER.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GO HOME.
Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE COACH LED UPOLU TO A
LANDSLIDE VICTORY.
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY!
SENDING SAVAII TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, WHERE PAPA BEAR TRIED
TO SAVE HIMSELF BY STEERING
VOTES TO COCHRAN.
PHYSICALLY, HE'S A THREAT TO
HIMSELF.
I DON'T NECESSARILY FEEL
THAT'S THE CASE.
Jeff: IN THE END, COCHRAN
PREVAILED.
PAPA BEAR, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SENDING PAPA BEAR TO JOIN
CHRISTINE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND,
WHERE THEY WILL COMPETE NAY DUEL
TO STAY ALIVE.
IS NERVE YOUR FAMILY AS
OUTDOORSY AND ATHLETIC AS YOU?
NO.
HOW DID YOU PICK THAT UP?
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE KID, I
JUST WAS REALLY INTO
SURVIVALISM.
LIKE THE FIRST BOOK THEY EVER
READ THAT MADE AN IMPRESSION WAS
"ROBINSON CARUSO."
I'M THINKING MAYBE LISA AND
OZZY HAVE A TIGHTER BOND THAN IS
REALIZED.
I KNOW THE GAME WELL ENOUGH TO
KNOW A PAIR IS VERY, VERY
POWERFUL.
AND THE THING IS, OSSIE'S
POWERFUL ENOUGH AS A PHYSICAL
PRESENCE IN THIS GAME, BUT YOU
CAN'T GET HIM THAT PHYSICAL
PRESENCE AND THAT VOTING
PRESENCE BECAUSE THEN HE WOULD
RUN IT LIKE ROB DID LAST YEAR.
I STARTED THINKING, IKE NOT
GOING TO GET OZZY OUT.
LISA'S GOD TO GO.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU MY
WHOLE STRATEGY.
OKAY, I'M READY TO HEAR IT.
OZZY REALIZES IF HE VOTES ME
OUT, HE'S INVALUABLE.
EVEN NOW I THINK HE'S SEEN AS
INVALUABLE.
NOW THERE'S A ROUNDING FACTOR
WITH ELYSE IN THE PICTURE, AND
HE'S USING ELYSE TO PLAY.
IN MY MIND SHE'S A VARIABLE, AND
I LIKE CONSTANTS IN THIS GAME.
I HATE DOING THIS, BUT WHAT IF
WE GET RID OF ELYSE.
THAT WAY THE VARIABLE IS GONE,
AND THE STRENGTH--
I THINK IT WOULD BE PRETTY
GOOD.
AND IT'S A MOVE.
IT'S A "SURVIVOR" MOVE.
I KNOW.
SHE'S SO FREAKING HOT.
I CAN POUT A SEE WE'D WIG.
HE'S A USED CAR SALESMAN SMILE
WITH WHITE TEETH THAT ARE
SUSPICIOUSLY WHITE TO ME.
HE WANTS ELYSE GONE NEXT WHICH
IS MUSIC TO ME.
IF ELYSE GOES FIRST, THAT BUYS
ME ANOTHER THREE DAYS AND WHO
KNOWS WHAT OZZY IS GOING TO DO.
I LIKE IT.
I DO.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
THIS GAME TO ME IS SO JACKED
UP WHEN IT COMES TO PEOPLE'S
FEELINGS.
I CAME INTO THIS GAME WITH GOOD
INTENTIONS, BUT IT WAS RUINED BY
MY PRIDE.
I LET MY PRIDE GET TO ME.
I STARTED GRAVITATING TOWARDS
EYE LINE OF PEOPLE, AND EVERY
DAY IS A STRUGGLE.
IT'S-- IT'S-- IT'S-- I CAN'T
TELL YOU TOMORROW THEY WON'T GET
UPSET, BUT FROM HERE ON OUT,
DECIDED TO BE A BETTER PERSON, A
BETTER PLAYER, A BETTER
"SURVIVOR."
I REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE
THAT.
I JUST GOT A LITTLE BIT UPSET
AND I SHOULDN'T HAVE LET MY
TEMPER GET AHOLD OF ME LIKE
THAT.
I APOLOGIZE AND I HOPE YOU
ACCEPT MY APOLOGY.
I APPRECIATE IT.
YOU KNOW, I UNDERSTAND, LIKE,
YOU'RE DOING THE RIGHT THING BY
APOLOGIZING, BUT, DUDE, MAYBE
YOU SHOULD THINK TWO OR THREE
TIMES BEFORE YOU TALK BECAUSE
IT'S JUST, LIKE, THE THING THAT
HE SHOULD HAVE DONE AND HE
APOLOGIZES.
IT JUST MAKES HIM LOOK LIKE A
FOOL.
BUT HIS UNCLE, LOOK WHO HIS
UNCLE IS.
THAT'S WHAT ALWAYS GETS ME--
LOOK WHO HIS UNCLE IS.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I KNOW I'M SCREWING THIS UP FOR
MYSELF AS FAR AS THE GAME IS
CONCERNED, BUT I CARE ABOUT YOU,
AND YOU'VE BEEN A VERY GOOD
FRIEND TO ME.
AND THIS WHOLE TIME I'VE KNOWN
THAT THE PEOPLE THAT YOU
TRUSTED, INCLUDING ME, LIED TO
YOU, AND I CAN'T LIE TO ANYBODY
ANYMORE.
THERE'S DEFINITELY A CORE FIVE.
LIKE I SAID, THIS IS PROBABLY
THE WORST GAME STRATEGY IN THE
WORLD.
THERE'S ONLY A CORE FIVE AND
NOT A CORE OF SIX?
THERE'S ALL KIND OF CORES.
I KNOW, THERE'S-- IT'S LIKE
THE ONION.
YEAH.
I'M SORRY.
AND I HOPE YOU ACCEPT MY
APOLOGY.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M JUST KIND OF SURPRISED ABOUT
THE CORE OF FIVE.
ARE YOU UPSET?
IT'S REALITY.
BRANDON PULLED ME ASIDE AND SAID
THAT I WAS ACTUALLY NOT PART OF
THE ALLIANCE OF 6.
HE SAID THAT THE OTHER FIVE
PEOPLE IN THE ALLIANCE HAD
BASICALLY JUST TOLERATED ME AND
THAT GIVEN THE OPPORTUNITY, I'D
BE THE NEXT TO GO.
IT WAS A TERRIBLE FEELING
BECAUSE YOU'RE BELIEVING THAT
YOU'RE PART OF THIS GROUP, AND
IT'S EASIER TO BELIEVE A LIE
SOMETIMES THAN IT IS TO ACCEPT
THE TRUTH.
TREE MAIL!
MY BATHING SUIT!
( CHEERS )
YA!
BEING MORMON I HAVE NEVER
FELT COMFORTABLE SWIMMING IN MY
UNDERWEAR AND BRA.
I HAVE NOT FELT COMFORTABLE
DOING THAT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF MINE ARE
SEE THROUGH.
FINALLY.
THE TREE MAIL SAYS, "TWO MORE
FROM YOUR TRIBE WILL VISIT THE
ARENA, A DECISION WHICH NEEDS TO
BE JUST.
WITNESS THEM BATTLE TO STAY IN
THIS GAME AND WATCH AS ONE BITES
THE DUST."
WHOA.
WHO WANTS TO GO?
I'LL-- I'LL GO.
I DON'T WANT TO GO.
I DON'T, EITHER.
THIS IS GOING WELL.
I'LL GO, I'LL GO.
OKAY.
I WANT TO GO BUT AT THE SAME
TIME I DON'T LIKE COCHRAN AND I
BOTH GOING AT THE SAME TIME
BECAUSE NOBODY KNOWS COCHRAN AND
I ARE TOGETHER, AND GUILT BY
ASSOCIATION--
NOBODY WANTS TO BE ALONE WITH
ME.
>>
NOT A WAY TO WIN THIS GAME.
WHOO-HOO!
MY NEW SWIMSUIT!
I HONESTLY THINK THE THING
THAT'S CONCERNED ME MOST IN THE
GAME IS MY AGE.
I LOVE IT.
IT'S A VERY CUTE BATHING SUIT.
IT'S A CUTE BATHING SUIT.
YEAH, SUPER CUTE.
AS I LOOKED AT THE OTHER
PEOPLE THAT ARE GOING TO BE
PLAYING IN THE GAME, I WAS
THINKING TO MYSELF, AM I RUDEO
THIS TRIBE?
I MEAN, I LOVED RUDY BUT FOR 40,
I'M ON THE OLD SIDE.
BUT I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO SHOW
THE THE SAVAII TRIBE WHAT I CAN
DO BECAUSE I THINK THERE ARE
SOME REALLY COMFORTABLE PAIRINGS
AND GROUPINGS AND THOSE MAY
ALREADY BE ALLIANCES, SO I FEEL
LIKE IT'S ABSOLUTELY CRITICAL
FOR ME TO PERFORM, NO QUESTION.
I CAN'T BE THE WEAKEST.
HERE'S MY THOUGHT PROCESS--
IF WE HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY, THE
OTHER TRIBE THINKING THAT WE'RE
WEAK MIGHT GET US SOME TYPE OF
PLAY.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
ALL ON THE SAME PAGE SO IF
SOMETHING COMES UP, SOME PEOPLE
WON AT THIS, SOME PEOPLE WON AT
THAT.
I REALLY THINK IT'S TOO EARLY
AT THIS POINT.
WE NEED TO PLANT THAT SEED NOW
AND GIVE THEM EXTRA FUEL.
IF YOU PLAN ON GOING FAR IN
THIS GAME, YOU DEFINITELY TRY TO
THINK A FEW STEPS AHEAD, BUT
JIMMY'S TRYING TO PLAY THE
STRATEGY POINT TOO MUCH.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
BYE!
SEE YOU IN A BIT.
HAVE FUN!
YA, THEY'RE GONE.
STRATEGY.
STRAIT.
STRATEGY, STRATEGY.
OH, LORD.
JIM, CON DOWN.
WE HAVE, LIKE, WEEKS.
CHILL OUT, BRO.
WHILE COCHRAN AND JIM WERE
WALKING OUT, THE FIRST THING
OZZY SAID WAS, "WE'RE NOT GOING
TO TALK STRATEGY," AND HE WAS
KIND OF MOCKING JIM, DON'T THINK
TOO MUCH STRATEGY.
I'M NOT SURE THAT'S HOW I'VE
SEEN OZZY PLAY THE GAME IN THE
PAST.
I THINK HE'S STRATEGIZING.
HE'S JUST DONE IT SOMEWHERE
ELSE, A DIFFERENT TIME AND
PLACE.
HE JUST DOESN'T WANT US
STRATEGIZING AND THAT IRKS ME TO
NO END.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
CHRISTINE WILL BE BATTLING
AGAINST PAPA BEAR VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
PAPA BEAR, HOW DOES IT FEEL TO
SEE COCHRAN AND JIM UP THERE,
TWO OF THE MEMBERS OF YOUR TRIBE
WHO VOTED YOU OUT OF THIS GAME
AND ARE NOW HERE TO WITNESS YOU
FIGHT FOR A CHANCE TO STAY IN
IT?
IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, THEY REALIZE THAT ONCE
I GET BACK IN THE GAME, I'M
GOING TO IMMEDIATELY GO TO THEM
AND GIVE THEM ANYTHING THEY
NEED.
Jeff: BRANDON, NICE TO HEAR
IF PAPA BEAR GETS BACK IN THIS
GAME, HE'S ALREADY TELLING YOU
RIGHT NOW, YOU GOT ME.
YEAH, I GUARANTEE THAT'S HOW
CHRISTINE IS FEELING, TOO, AND
THAT'S THAT I'D DO THAT MYSELF.
ACTUALLY, I WOULD LIKE TO SAY
SOMETHING TO CHRISTINE, IF YOU
DON'T MIND.
Jeff: SHE'S NOT LOOKING UP,
BUT I'M GUESSING SHE CAN HEAR.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I JUST WANT
TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU FOR THE WAY
THAT I HANDLED THAT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, AND I CAME CLEAN TO
EVERYBODY.
I FEEL REALLY BAD THE FIRST
SEVEN DAYS I PLAYED THIS GAME, I
PLAYED IST RUTHLESS, AND I
TURNED OVER A NEW LEAF.
I'M SORRY, CHRISTINE.
I HOPE YOU TO WELL.
Jeff: CHRISTINE, DO YOU
ACCEPT BRANDON'S APOLOGY?
I ACCEPT IT.
WHETHER I BUY IT OR NOT IS A
DIFFERENT STORY.
Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S DUEL?
YES.
Jeff: FOR TODAY'S DUEL YOU
WILL TOSS SANDBAGS ATTEMPTING TO
LAND THE BAGS ON TOP OF CRATES.
THE FIRST PERSON TO GET ONE BAG
ON EACH OF THE 10 CRATES STAYS
ALIVE IN THIS GAME, WILL LIVE TO
SEE ANOTHER DAY.
THE LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD.
THIS IS IT, ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ONE BAG AT A TIME.
PAPA BEAR LANDS HIS FIRST.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER FIRST.
OOH!
Jeff: PAPA BEAR SHORT.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER SECOND.
DON'T BE AFRAID TO GIVE IT A
LITTLE HEIGHT.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER THIRD.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER FOURTH.
PAPA BEAR WITH HIS SECOND.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER FIFTH.
SHE'S ON IT!
Jeff: PAPA BEAR LANDS HIS
THIRD.
OH!
Jeff: CHRISTINE GOES LONG,
JUST MISSES.
PAPA BEAR WITH HIS FOURTH.
IT IS NOW 5-4.
GET ON THERE.
Jeff: CHRISTINE WITH HER
SIXTH.
YOU WANT A SHOT BACK IN THIS
GAME, YOU GOTTA WIN THIS
CHALLENGE RIGHT NOW.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER SEVENTH BAG.
PAPA BEAR LANDS HIS FIFTH.
HE'S BACK IN IT.
OH!
Jeff: CHRISTINE JUST
MISSES.
PAPA BEAR LANDS HIS SIXTH!
WE'VE GOT A DUEL.
OH!
Jeff: CHRISTINE LANDS HER
EIGHTH.
PAPA BEAR WITH HIS SEVENTH.
IT IS 8-7.
CHRISTINE IS HOVERING ALL AROUND
HER NINTH CRATE.
JUST CAN'T GET IT TO STICK.
CHRISTINE STICKS IT.
ONE IS JUST HANGING ON.
OH, AND IT DROPS!
CHRISTINE'S NINTH BAG DROPS OFF
AND SHE IS BACK TO EIGHT.
IT IS 8-7.
PAPA BEAR LANDS HIS EIGHTH.
WE ARE TIED, 8-8.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER NINTH.
PAPA BEAR GOTTA KEEP MOVING.
PAPA BEAR HAS HIS NINTH.
WE ARE TIED 9-9.
EACH TOSS COUNTS.
PAPA BEAR ON AND OFF.
LOSE HERE, YOU ARE GOING HOME.
CHRISTINE LANDS HER TENTH AND
LIVES TO SEE ANOTHER DAY!
YOU DID GOOD.
Jeff: PAPA BEAR, NOW THAT
THIS JOURNEY ON "SURVIVOR" IS
COMING TOAB END, DO YOU GO BACK
TO THAT TIME WHEN THIS DREAM TO
BE ON THE SHOW BEGAN?
YOU KNOW, WHEN I SAW
"SURVIVOR" I SAID, SOME DAY I'M
GOING TO BE ON THAT SHOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GOING TO
GET ON THAT SHOW BUT SOME DAY
I'M GOING TO AWE DECISION ON
THAT SHOW.
AND ALL THE COPS AND FIREMEN,
EVERYBODY WHO WAS THERE WERE
LIKE, "OH, YEAH, YOU'LL GET ON,
HA-HA."
AND NOW TO FULFILL THAT DREAM, I
FEEL BLESSED.
Jeff: PAPA BEAR, YOUR
ADVENTURE HAS COME TO AN END.
IT IS TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
SEE YOU IN THE BIG APPLE.
Jeff: HAVE A GOOD ONE.
THANKS.
IN THE FIRE?
Jeff: YEAH.
CHRISTINE, CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: TWO DUELS IN A ROW.
YOU LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND, AND AWAIT
YOUR NEXT OPPONENT.
THANK YOU.
I WANT THE SPECTATORS TO SEE
THAT I'M NOT OUT.
AT ALL.
AND I'M STILL IN IT, AND THERE'S
STILL A FIGHT LEFT IN ME, AND
THEY'LL SEE IT.
THAT'S WHAT THEY WANT TO SEE.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE GOING TO
GET.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
DO YOU WANT MILK OR NO MILK?
FRANKLY, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
LIKE, ANY COFFEE IS BETTER THAN
NO COFFEE.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH MILK.
KNOWING WHAT BRANDON TOLD ME
IS GOING TO MAKE ME MORE
CAUTIOUS OF TRUSTING THE
INDIVIDUALS IN MY ALLIANCE, SO
FOR ME IT'S IMPORTANT TO BE
CORDIAL AND POLITE.
I'M GOING TO WASH MY SHIRT AND
TROUSERS.
YOU WANT TO WASH YOUR SHIRT AND
PANTS WHILE I'M AT IT?
NAH.
NOT GETTING TOO STIFF?
A LITTLE STIFF.
IT'S A SOCIAL GAME AND I HAVE
TO EMPHASIZE THE SOCIAL GAME
ASPECT OF MY STRATEGY BECAUSE
PHYSICALLY I CAN'T WIN AGAINST
THOSE PEOPLE.
EDNA?
YES, SIR.
WOULD YOU MIND, LIKE, LATER
IF WE'RE LAYING ON THAT BEECH
OVER THERE TO WALK ON MY BACK.
I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
I CAN WALK ON ANYBODY.
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S LIKE RICOCHET RABBIT.
THE GIRL GO ON AND ON AND ON AND
ON AND ON.
DOES SHE HAVE AN OFF SWITCH?
I DON'T THINK SHE HAS AN OFF
SWITCH.
SHE NEEDS TO BE DISCONNECTED.
THAT'S WHAT SHE NEEDS TO BE,
DISCONNECTED.
WHEN YOU MODEL WHAT KIND OF
GIGS DO YOU DO?
IS IT TV OR PRINT?
SOME PRINT.
I'VE BEEN ON THE COVER OF A
COUPLE OF THINGS.
THAT'S COOL.
LIKE WHAT HOW DO YOU GET
RECRUITED?
THEY E-MAIL ME ABOUT DATES
AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
THAT'S SO COOL.
I'LL HAVE TO GO LOOK FOR IT.
GET YOUR AUTOGRAPH.
FOR REAL.
EDNA ASKS SO MANY DARN
QUESTIONS.
AT ONE POINT I ANSWERED JUST TO
SHUT HER UP.
YESTERDAY RICK WAS TALKING ABOUT
HOW HE GOES HUNTING AND SHOT A
BUFFALO.
HOW MANY TIMES DO YOU SHOOT HIM.
WHAT DID YOU AIM WITH?
ARE YOU, EDNA, EVER GOING TO GO
HUNTING FOR A BUFFALO?
NO, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
ZIP IT.
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
REALLY, WHERE DOES IT HURT?
JUST KEEP DOING WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
THIS IS AMAZING.
AND HER LITTLE LAUGH.
OH!
IT'S GOING TO HAUNT ME WHEN I
GET HOME.
HEE-HEE-HEE.
SHUT UP.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS THE FUNNIEST THING
EVER.
OH, GOD.
AND I JUST THINK THAT'S
BALONEY.
HE ALREADY HAS IT LOCKED OR HE'S
TRYING TO GET OTHER PEOPLE TO
NOT TALK.
WE JUST NEED TO GO SOMETHING
I THINK BECAUSE THE FORGONE
CONCLUSION MIGHT BE THAT IT'S
GONNA BE ME, MAYBE YOU.
JIM AND I DEVELOPED A GOOD
PARTNERSHIP MOVING FORWARD.
BUT NUMERICALLY, IT DOESN'T SEEM
COMPLETELY STRAIGHTFORWARD THAT
WE'RE GOING TO BE ABLE TO GET
RID OF ELYSE BECAUSE RIGHT NOW
IT'S JIM AND I ON BOARD TO VOTE
FOR ELYSE.
THERE HAS TO BE SOMEBODY ELSE
WILLING TO DO THIS OR ELSE WE'RE
SCREWED.
OZZY.
I WAS TALKING TO, UM, JIM,
AND I DON'T THINK JIM'S FOND OF
GETTING RID OF OZZY.
WHO IS CLOSEST TO ODE?
ELYSE?
I THINK SHE'S IN OZZY'S BACK
POCKET.
IF THEY'RE NOT COOL WITH
TAKING OZZY OUT NOW, IT HAS TO
BE ELYSE.
IT TURNS OUT DAWN IS ALSO
KIND OF ON THE SAME AND I THINK
WANTS ELYSE OUT, AND SOMEBODY
LIKE ME WHO THRIVES ON BIG
STRATEGIC MOVES AND LOVES SEEING
THAT IN A GAME LIKE "SURVIVOR"
I'VE BEEN DYING TO BE A PART OF
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
GETTING RID OF ELYSE IS GOING TO
DEVASTATE OZZY AND IT MIGHT MAKE
THE OTHER PRETTY PEOPLE FEEL A
LITTLE BIT LESS SECURE.
THIS IS FINALLY GOING TO BE THE
TIME WHEN THE SAVAII TRIBE MAKES
A MOVE THAT IS GOING TO CHANGE
THE COURSE OF THE GAME AND IT'S
GOING TO SURPRISE A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YEAH!
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
WILL TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, THREE
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL HAVE
A POLE ACROSS THEIR SHOULDERS
EACH ROUND WEIGHT WILL BE ADD TO
THAT POLE.
THE DECISION ABOUT WHICH MEMBER
GET THE WEIGHT WILL BE MADE BY
THE OTHER TRIBE.
WHEN THE WEIGHT BECOMES TOO MUCH
TO BEAR, YOU'LL DROP THE POLE,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY FOR THEIR TRIBE.
YOU WILL BE SAFE AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNING TRIBE
EARNS REWARD.
CHICKENS.
WHOOO!
( APPLAUSE ).
OH, YEAH!
Jeff: ONE ROOSTER, TWO
HENS, EGGS OR THE OTHER.
THE WINNING TRIBE WILL ALSO
RECEIVE ANOTHER NOTE TO THE
LOCATION OF THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
THIS CHALLENGE REQUIRES TWO MEN
AND ONE WOMAN TO BE THE WEIGHT
BEARERS.
GIVE YOU GUYS A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR WEIGHT
BEARERS.
FOR SAVAII, KEITH, DAWN, AND
JIM.
FOR UPOLU, WE HAVE BRANDON,
STACEY, AND ALBERT.
YOU WILL ASSIGN WEIGHT TO ONE
PERSON TO THE OPPOSING TRIBE.
SAVAII, WHO YOU GOING TO PUT THE
WEIGHT ON FIRST?
WE'RE GOING WITH ALBERT
FIRST.
Jeff: UPOLU,.
KEITH.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LODE THE
WEIGHT.
EACH BAG AWAYS 10 POUNDS SO EACH
TIME YOU ARE PUTTING 20 POUNDS
ON SOMEBODY.
HERE WE GO, THREE, TWO, ONE.
DROP THE WEIGHT.
THAT IS HOW IT GOES.
HERE WE GO, NEXT ROUND.
UPOLU, WHERE ARE YOU PUTTING
WEIGHT?
JIM.
Jeff: JIM'S GETTING WEIGHT.
BRANDON.
Jeff: AND BRANDON IS
GETTING WEIGHT.
I SPENT 11 DAYS DROPPING 20
POUND.
Jeff: HERE WE GO, THREE,
TWO, ONE.
RELEASE THE WEIGHT.
SAVAII, WHO YOU GOING TO PUT
WEIGHT ON?
STACEY.
Jeff: UPOLU.
DAWN.
Jeff: BOTH TRIBES SPREADING
THE WEIGHT AROUND EARLY IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
Jeff: HERE'S WHERE WE
STAND.
DAWN AND STACEY AT 100 POUND.
ALBERT AND KEITH AT 180.
JIM AND BRANDON EACH AT 200
POUNDS.
YOU GOTTA, KEITH.
YOU KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
Jeff: KEITH REALLY STRUG
LING TO HANG IN THERE.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO GET THAT
BAR BACK UP ON HIS SHOULDERS.
YOU CAN'T HOLD IT THAT WAY FOR
LONG.
YOUR ARMS ARE GOING TO GIVE OUT.
KEITH TRYING TO GET IT BACK UP
ON HIS SHOULDERS.
DIG DEEP, KEITH, YOU CAN DO
IT.
Jeff: KEITH IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE AT 180 POUNDS.
SAVAII NOW DOWN TO TWO MEMBERS
LEFT.
UPOLU HAS ALL THREE.
NEXT ROUND, SAVAII?
BRANDON IS THERE BRANDON.
AND.
JIM.
Jeff: THIS WILL TIE THE
RECORD OF 320 POUNDS HELD BY
RUPERT, J.T., AND BRANDON.
NO, NO, NO!
DAMN IT!
Jeff: ALBERT IS OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
DAMN IT!
Jeff: WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR,
JIM AND DAWN, BRANDON AND
STACEY, JIM AND BRANDON BOTH
ABOUT TO GET WEIGHT.
YOU CAN DO IT, JIM!
Jeff: HERE WE GO, THREE,
TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
YOU GOT THIS, JIM.
HANG IN THERE, JIM!
Jeff: JIM AND BRANDON BOTH
HOLDING STRONG AT 220 POUNDS.
YOU'RE NOW PART OF SURVIVOR
HISTORY.
LET'S LODE SOME MORE WEIGHT.
SAVAII, WHO IS GETTING THE
WEIGHT?
BRANDON.
JIM.
Jeff: BRANDON AND JIM
GETTING WEIGHT.
THIS WOULD BE A NEW "SURVIVOR"
RECORD.
YOU GOT THIS, JIM.
>>
Jeff: 240 POUND SQUEAK HAVE
TWO GUYS SHOWING DOWN, JIM AND
BRANDON.
THREE, TWO, ONE, RELEASE.
WAY TO GO, JIM!
Jeff: VERY IMPRESSIVE.
A NEW "SURVIVOR" RECORD FOR JIM
AND BRANDON.
240 POUNDS.
JIM CANNOT HANG ON ANY LONGER.
JIM IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
BRANDON STRUGGLING TO HANG IN
THERE.
HOLD IT!
Jeff: BRANDON AT 240
STRUGGLING TO HANG IN THERE.
EVERYTHING HE HAS.
BRANDON IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
DAWN, DAWN, YOU'RE AWESOME!
Jeff: WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS DAWN AND STACEY FIGHTING
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
NEXT ROUND.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICES.
LOAD THEM UP.
HOLD ON, BABY.
Jeff: STACEY'S HANGING ON
BY HER BUTT.
THIS COULD BE IT.
THIS WILL BRING BOTH DAWN AND
STASE TOW 120 POUNDS.
YOU CAN DO IT!
Jeff: HERE WE GO.
ADD THE WEIGHT, THREE, TWO, ONE.
AND RELEASE.
A GREAT EFFORT BY DAWN AND
STACEY.
THERE WE GO, STACEY.
WAY TO GO, DAWN.
I'M KIND OF LOSING IT ON MY
BACK.
GOUT IT, DAWN.
HANG IN THERE, DAWN.
YOU'VE COME SO FAR, DAWN.
YOU CAN DO THIS, DAWN!
Jeff: LET'S GO.
LOAD THEM UP AGAIN.
YOU GOT IT, STACEY.
Jeff: THIS WILL PUT STACEY
AT 140 AND DAWN AT 140.
DAWN READJUSTING.
NOT A GOOD TIME TO READJUST.
DAWN NOW SLIDING DOWN HER BACK.
YOU'RE GOING TO WIN THIS FOR
US, DAWN!
BOUNCE IT OUT.
Jeff: HERE WE GO, THREE,
TWO, ONE, AND RELEASE
( APPLAUSE ).
YES, STASE!
YOU CAN DO IT!
COME ON, STACEY!
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE, DAWN.
LET'S GO, BABY.
YOU GOT THIS!
THAT IS A GIRL, STACEY.
YOU'RE SO STRONG, DAWN.
YOU'RE STRONGER THAN THIS.
Jeff: LEGS ARE WOBBLING BUT
STACEY NOT GIVING IN.
HANG IN THERE, DAWN.
YOU LOOK SOLID.
Jeff: YOU CANNOT LET GO
NOW!
YOU CAN DO THIS.
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO FIND IT
INSIDE YOURSELF.
YOU GOT MORE INSIDE THAT TANK.
DAWN, YOU GOT IT.
YOU CAN DO IT.
Jeff: THIS IS IT.
YOU GOT IT, STASE.
DIG REAL DEEP.
THAT'S A GIRL, STACEY.
THAT A GIRL, STACEY!
YES!
YEAH!
Jeff: DAWN WINS FOR SAVAII!
AWESOME!
OH, MY GOSH.
AWESOME, DAWN.
YOU GUYS DID GREAT.
I DID IT!
Jeff: DAWN, I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY WILL CARE IF I GIVE THIS
TO YOU.
THANK YOU!
Jeff: NICE JOB.
ALL RIGHT, SAVAII,
CONGRATULATIONS.
COME GET YOUR REWARD.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I'VE BEEN THROUGH A TOUGH DAY
ONE DAY, CAME BACK FEELING
REALLY STRONG AND LIKE I HAD A
LOT TO CONTRIBUTE AND THEN TO BE
THE LAST PERSON STANDING IN THAT
CHALLENGE TODAY, I ALMOST DIDN'T
BELIEVE IT.
IT FELT SO GOOD.
I COULDN'T BREATHE.
Jeff: UPOLU, TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME AND SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
THE CHALLENGE WE DIDN'T WIN,
BUT I THINK I DID JUST FINE.
I HELD UP 140 POUND SO I DO
BELIEVE I PROVED TO THEM THAT I
HAVE STRENGTH, MORE THAN ANY ONE
OF THE GIRLS.
BUT, YOU KNOW, LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, I GOT THE VOTES.
SO IT COULD BE ME, COULD NOT BE
ME.
THAT'S WHAT A BLINDSIDE IS.
I COULD BE BLINDSIDED.
GOOD JOB.
YOU DID A HELL OF A JOB.
STACEY, FEELING ALL RIGHT?
OH, I'M GETTING THERE.
THAT WAS PRETTY AWESOME.
WHAT.
STACEY.
YOU HAD 60 POUNDS, AND IT WAS
LIKE THIS WAY.
THEY JUST KEPT LOADING ON THE
WEIGHT.
WHAT WAS YOUR FINAL WEIGHT?
100 AND SOMETHING.
140?
IT WAS UP THERE, I KNOW.
THEY BOTH GOT PRETTY HIGH.
LET'S NOT GET TOO DOWN,
RIGHT?
YOU DID GREAT.
WHAT'S DONE IT DONE.
WE HAVE FOUGHT IT IN THE PAST.
WE HAVE TO PICK OURSELVES UP AND
WE LIVE TO FIGHT ANOTHER DAY.
I FEEL PRETTY CONFIDENT
WITHIN MY ALLIANCE, BUT AT THE
SAME TIME, I HAVE THAT LITTLE
VOICE IN ME THAT SAYS EVERYBODY
PERCEIVES ME AS WEAKEST LINK IN
THE TRIBE, AND SO I JUST WANT TO
MAKE SURE THAT I'M ABSOLUTELY
SAFE AND I WON'T FEEL SAFE UNTIL
AFTER TRIBAL TONIGHT.
I HAVE A SUSPICION THAT THE
TRIBE SUSPECTS THAT I'M THE
WEAKEST LINK.
I DON'T KNOW.
COYOU THINK I SHOULD PACK ALL
MY STUFF TONIGHT?
YOU DO WHAT YOU THINK YOU
HAVE TO DO.
I DON'T KNOW.
EDNA IS LIKE ON AN EASTER EGG
HUNT RIGHT NOW.
SHE IS SCRAMBLING LIKE SCRAMBLED
EGGS IN A HOT SKILLET RIGHT NOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>>?
YOU AIN'T TALKED TO ME SINCE DAY
ONE.
AND NOW YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME
BECAUSE IT'S EITHER ME OR YOU.
THAT SHOULD VOTE EDNA OVER ME.
LOOK WHAT I LISTED TODAY.
CAN EDNA LIST 20?
I DOUBT IT.
YOU CAN'T LIFT TOO MUCH IF IT'S
ALL SKELETON WITH THE BONE.
HOW YOU DOING?
PULLING MYSELF TOGETHER.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
BUMMED.
I CAN TELL EVERYBODY IS
BUMMED, YOU KNOW.
NOBODY WANTS TO GO HOME.
I KNOW I DON'T.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE I STAND.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE I STAND?
DO YOU?
IT'S EITHER YOU OR SOMEBODY
ELSE.
OR EDNA.
I CAN'T LIE TO YOU.
YEAH, I KNOW EYE DON'T KNOW
WHAT SHE REALLY BRINGS TO THE
TABLE.
BUT EVERYTHING THAT I'VE DONE
AROUND HERE, I PULLED MY WEIGHT.
I KNOW.
I DIDN'T MASSAGE YOUR BACK,
BUT, UH...
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
I'M GOING TO MOVE OFF.
OKAY.
I DON'T WANT TO FALL IN THE
FIRE.
I'M NOT BUYING COACH'S
B.S. AT ALL.
THAT LOYALTY, GAME PLAYING
STUFF, I DON'T BUY THAT
WHATSOEVER.
BUT YOU KNOW, I'M NOT GIVING UP.
I AIN'T QUITTING, SO I'M NOT A
REALLY BIG LIAR.
I HAVE TO LIE WHILE I'M HERE.
I HAVE TO LIE TO KICK IT, AND
CHA WHATTHAT MEANS IS I HAVE TO
LIE TO GET IN TO FIT IN, LIE TO
KICK IT WITH THE NEXT MAN.
HAVE YOU AND ALBERT TALKED
YET?
UH-HUH.
WHAT HAVE THEY BEEN TALKING
ABOUT?
NOTHING.
WHAT THEY BEEN DOING.
WHO?
THE GUYS.
IF YOU NAME, NAMES I'LL
FIGURE OUT WHAT EXACTLY YOU'RE
SAYING.
WHO ARE THE PEOPLE YOU WENT
OFF ON?
OH, ALBERT, SOPHIE, AND
MIKAYLA.
STACEY CAME UP TO ME AND SAID
YOU REALLY GOTTA KEEP YOUR EYE
OUT FOR MIKAYLA, SOPHIE, AND
ALBERT.
I WOULD REALLY LIKE TO THINK
THAT EVERYBODY'S KEEPING THEIR
PROMISE.
AS FAR AS THE FINAL FIVE, IT'S
"SURVIVOR."
EVERYONE'S OUT FOR THEIRED
SELVES.
IT'S A REALLY SELFISH GAME SO
YOU HAVE TO DO WHAT YOU HAVE TO
DO TO WIN.
COACH, WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM ON
OUR HANDS.
ANOTHER ONE?
YEAH, BUDDY.
WE DON'T HAVE A FIVE ALLIANCE.
IT MIGHT BE THE END OF THE ROAD
AS FAR AS THAT GOES.
STACEY JUST CAME UP TO ME WHILE
WE WERE GONE, SHE CAME UP TO ME
AND SAID THAT ALBERT, MIKAYLA,
AND SOPHIE HAVE SOMETHING GOING
ON.
STOP IT.
I'M CONTINGENT YOU.
NO, I WANT YOU TO STOP IT.
STOP.
LOOK AT ME.
DUDE, LOOK AT ME.
THIS GAME IS GOING TO GET SO
MUCH CRAZIER THAN THIS.
AND IF YOU BELIEVE SOMEBODY--
TELL ME IF SOMEBODY IS SNEAK UP
ON ME-- IF YOU BELIEVE SOMEBODY
THAT IS ON DEATH ROW, LIKE
STACEY KNOWS SHE IS, OVER
SOMEBODY THAT IS IN OUR CORE
ALLIANCE, THEN YOU MIGHT AS WELL
THROW IN THE TOWEL RIGHT NOW.
I'M TELLING YOU.
I TONIGHT CARE WHAT SHE SAYS.
YOU HAVE ONE PERSON TELL YOU
SOMETHING OUTSIDE OF OUR
ALLIANCE, AND YOU'RE BITING IT
EVERY TIME.
I CAN SEE THAT IT'S, LIKE,
YOU'RE ALREADY THINKING THAT
IT'S FACT.
DON'T WORRY, MAN.
LOOK AT ME JUST FOR A SECOND--
I'M JUST CURIOUS HOW MANY
PEOPLE SCREWED YOU IN THE PAST
TWO GAMES YOU PLAYED.
BECAUSE BOTH GAMES I WAS--
BOTH GAMES--
I'M JUST GIVING YOU AN
EXAMPLE.
BECAUSE BOTH GAMES I HAD MY
HEAD IN THE SAND AND I WASN'T
PLAYING THE GAME.
I'M JUST TRYING TO GET IN THE
GAME AND READ PEOPLE AND I TEND
TO BE A GOOD JUDGE OF CHARACTER.
YOU OKAY, SOPHIE?
YEAH.
I THOUGHT I HAD A FIVE STRONG
PLUS EDNA ALLIANCE GOING.
AND IT SEEMS LIKE WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO DO SOME RESHUFFLING ONLY
BECAUSE OUR ALLIANCE IS BASED ON
TRUST, AND JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
IN IT DOESN'T MEAN, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE ALWAYS GOING TO TRUST YOU.
WE'LL TRUST YOU UNTIL YOU DO
SOMETHING WRONG AND RIGHT NOW IT
LOOKS MORE AND MORE LIKE BRANDON
IS A SMALL, SMALL RESULTS HANTZ.
I THINK THAT BRANDON IS A
GREAT GUY, AND I WANT TO BE WITH
BRANDON EVERY STEP OF THE WAY,
BUT I'M WORRIED HE IS GOING TO
KICK OVER THE KETTLE AT THE MOST
INOPPORTUNE TIME AND RUIN THE
GAME FOR EVERYBODY, AND THAT'S
WHY I HAVE TO ALSO PROTECT
MYSELF.
I HAVE TO REMEMBER THAT I'M OUT
HERE FOR THE THIRD AND POSSIBLY
FINAL TIME AND THIS HAS GOT TO
BE MY GAME, AND I CAN'T LET
ANYBODY OR ANYTHING MESS IT UP.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT TODAY'S
CHALLENGE.
IT CAME DOWN TO STACEY AND DAWN.
TWO WOMEN WHO REALLY DUKED IT
OUT.
STACEY, WHAT FINALLY HAPPENED?
I MEAN, YOU SAW ME ON MY
BACK.
I WAS ON MY KNEES, ONE ARM.
AND I HELD ON, HARD AS I COULD,
BUT I KNOW I WAS STRONG, AND I
DID A VERY GOOD JOB DURING THE
TIME.
Jeff: COACH, IT'S GOOD
NEWS/BAD NEWS TO BE PERSON WHO
CAN BE THE HERO OR THE GOAT.
YOU CAN ARGUE STACEY GAVE A HELL
OF AN EFFORT.
YOU CAN ALSO OFFER STACEY LOST
IT DAWN.
YOU KNOW, I THINK IF WE WERE
TRYING TO CHOOSE BETWEEN TWO
PEOPLE SOLELY BASED ON THEIR
WARRIOR SPIRIT, WOULD I SAY THAT
STACEY WAS ON THE FENCE TODAY?
NO.
WE ALL TAKE OUR HATS OFF TO HER
FOR HOW SHE PERFORMED IN THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
Jeff: ONE OF THE THINGS
THIS TRIBE HAS SAID FROM DAY ONE
IS WE'RE ALWAYS GOING TO KEEP
THE TRIBE STRONG.
EVERYBODY HERE AGREE WITH THAT?
YEAH.
Jeff: SO, SOPHIE, HOW IS
STRENGTH DEFINED RIGHT NOW ON
THIS TRIBE?
I THINK YOU LOOK AT STRENGTH
AS IN STRENGTH IN NUMBERS AS
WELL AS PHYSICAL STRENGTH
BECAUSE YOU COME TO THE MERGE
AND YOU'RE NOT SURE ABOUT
SOMETHING, THAT'S NOT A NUMBER.
THAT'S LESS OF A TRIBE.
I THINK WE'RE TRYING TO BALANCE
THE PHYSICAL STRENGTH AND TEAM
UNITY STRENGTH.
Jeff: OKAY, LET'S TRY A
LITTLE GROUP THERAPY.
RICK, ANSWER THIS QUESTION-- THE
MOST ANNOYING THING ABOUT ALBERT
IS...?
HE SNORES.
Jeff: WHAT'S THAT?
HE S'MORES.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S KIND OF A LAME
ANSWER.
BUT --
BRANDON, THE MOST ANNOYING
THING ABOUT EDNA IS WHAT?
SHE'S GOT A LOT TO SAY ABOUT
A LOT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT BAD.
IT'S JUST SOMETIMES IT GETS A
LITTLE BIT TOO MUCH.
BUT OTHER THAN THAT, I MEAN,
SHE'S JUST GOT A LOT OF
OPINIONS.
Jeff: EDNA, DOES THAT RING
TRUE TO YOU?
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
YOKE I'M OUT THERE VOICING MY
OPINION AND THOUGHTS ON EVER
SINGLE THING THAT OCCURS AT
CAMP.
EDNA, THE MOST ANNOYING THING
ABOUT STACEY IS WHAT?
I FIND IT VERY DIFFICULT TO
ENGAGE STACEY.
I'VE TRIED MANY TIMES TO GET TO
KNOW HER, OTHER THAN THAN SOME
SUPERFICIAL THINGS AND I DON'T
FEEL SHE OPENS UP AND THAT IS IS
WHAT I FIND THE MOST ANNOYING.
Jeff: STACEY, IS IT HARD
FOR YOU TO OPEN UP?
IT'S NOT HARD FOR ME TO OPEN
UP.
I'VE SPOKEN ABOUT MYSELF TO
QUITE A FEW OF THE PEOPLE SO I
DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE'S LOOKING
FOR, HOW MUCH SHE'S WANTING FROM
ME.
YOU KNOW, SHE ASKS, I GIVE HER
WHAT SHE ASKS FOR.
Jeff: MIKAYLA, THE MOST
ANNOYING THING ABOUT BRANDON?
HE'S A GREAT KID, BUT IT'S
ALWAYS IN THE BACK OF MY MIND
WHO HIS UNCLE IS.
Jeff: WHO IS HIS UNCLE?
RUSSELL.
Jeff: SO YOU SHARED WHO
YOUR UNCLE IS?
ABSOLUTELY.
AND HE SAYS HE'S NOTHING LIKE
HIM AND THIS OR THAT BUT IT'S
ONE THING THAT'S JUST, DARN,
YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD KID BUT WHY
DOES THAT HAVE TO BE YOUR UNCLE?
Jeff: IF HE'S SUCH A GOOD
KID, WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT
MAKE WHO YOUR UNCLE IS.
STILL, BLOOD IS BLOOD.
Jeff: BRANDON, IT SOUNDS
LIKE MIKAYLA IS SAYING AT A
CENSUS POINT HE'LL TURN INTO THE
WEREWOLF BECAUSE HE CAN'T HELP
IT.
IT'S IN THE BLOOD.
i AM PROUD OF BEING A HANTZ.
I LOVE MY UNCLE WITH ALL MY
HEART.
IT DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE THE SAME
PEOPLE.
HE CAME ON THE SHOW AND DID A
GREAT JOB.
HIS STRATEGY DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
MY STRATEGY.
I'M HERE TO PLAY WITHSTANDON'S
GIM.
I DON'T HAVE TO PROVE ANYTHING
TO ANYBODY BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE I
DO HERE.
Jeff: HOW DIFFICULT IS IT,
BRANDON TO HEAR PEOPLE TALK ILL
OF YOUR UNCLE?
IT'S TOUGH.
HE'S MY FAMILY.
IT'S JUST SOMETIMES WE FALL TO
TEMPTATION.
SOMETIMES WE JUST-- THIS CAN GET
HARD FOR EVERYBODY.
Jeff: WHAT'S UPSETTING TOO
YOU RIGHT NOW?
( SIGHS ).
BECAUSE, MAN, I JUST WANT TO
BE SOMEBODY THAT GOD'S PROUD OF.
AND...
Jeff: WHAT-- WHAT'S MAKING
YOU THINK YOU AREN'T?
I DON'T WANT TO BE
MISREPRESENTED TO MY FAMILY
BECAUSE IT AFFECTED MY FAMILY
BIG TIME WHEN THIS WHOLE THING
WENT DOWN WITH RUSSELL.
AND YOU CAN ONLY PROTECT HIM SO
MUCH, BUT WHEN YOU SEE WHAT HE
DONE, IT'S LIKE THE PROOF'S IN
THE PUDDING.
YOU CAN'T HELP SOMEBODY WHO HAS
DONE THAT TO HIMSELF, BUT WHAT
DO YOU DO?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
Jeff: SO YOU FEEL
RESPONSIBILITY TO RECLAIM THE
FAMILY NAME IN A POSITIVE LIGHT?
I'M GOING TO DO IT.
YOU KNOW, IF I HAVEN'T ALREADY
TOLD THEM ALREADY, I'M GOING TO
DO IT.
IT'S NOT HOW YOU START.
IT'S HOW YOU FINISH.
Jeff: ALBERT, PRETTY
EMOTIONAL STORY, BRANDON JUST
SHARED.
AND YET, WE ARE STILL IN A GAME.
HIS UNCLE'S A MASTER
MANIPULATOR.
SO, ALBERT, DOES THAT MEAN THE
NUMBER ONE TOPIC FOR TRIBAL
COUNCIL SHOULD BE TRUST?
YEAH, TRUST IS CERTAINLY
SOMETHING ON EVERYBODY'S MIND.
AND IT'S SOMETHING THAT IS A
CONTRIBUTING FACTOR TO THE VOTE
TONIGHT.
Jeff: ON THAT NOTE, IT IS
TIME TO VOTE.
RICK, YOU'RE UP.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTE ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, EDNA.
STACEY.
ONE VOTE STACEY.
TWO VOTES STACEY.
ONE VOTE EDNA.
STACEY.
THAT'S THREE VOTE STACEY, ONE
VOTE EDNA.
STACEY.
THAT'S FOUR VOTE STACEY.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC,"
STACEY.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
LET'S ALL GIVE HER A HUG.
COME ON, COME ON.
NO, NO.
Jeff: AFTER ALL THAT, THEY
OFFERED YOU A HUG.
IT'S NOT REAL.
EVERYTHING WAS A LIE THAT WAS
SAID TODAY.
SO... I WILL BE BACK.
Jeff: STACEY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
MOST DEFINITELY.
Jeff: GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
Jeff: WELL, BASED ON WHAT I
HEARD AND JUST SAW, TRUST AND
UNITY ARE TWO OF THE QUALITIES
YOU'RE ATTEMPTING TO BASE THIS
TRIBE ON, BUT AS WE JUST
WITNESSED, THEY ARE ALSO TWO OF
THE MOST DIFFICULT ASPECTS OF
THIS GAME TO MAINTAIN.
I WISH YOU LUCK.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
IF ANYBODY CALLS ME BENJAMIN
TO MY FACE I'M GOING TO GO NUTS.
BENJAMIN.
Jeff: THEY'RE GETTING TO
KNOW EACH OTHER IN A WHOLE NEW
WAY.
COACH WITH SOMETHING BIG.
WORST-CASE SCENARIO, I HAVE
HORRIBLE HERPES.
Jeff: THIS IS A DISGUSTING
CHALLENGE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
HELLO?
HEY!
AND THEY TALK ABOUT LOYALTY.
YOU NEED TO BE LOYAL TO NOBODY
BUT GOD.
THEY ARE LOYAL TO THEIR GOD,
WHICH IS COACH.
WHEN THE REDEMPTION TRIBE COMES
I'M GOING TO SPILL EVERYTHING
THAT IS GOING ON OVER THERE.
GUESS WHO IS RUNNING THINGS?
COACH.