Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": BY DAY 14, THE TWO
RETURN PLAYERS, OZZY AND COACH
WERE HEADING IN OPPOSITE
DIRECTIONS.
AT UPOLU, COACH'S CONTROL OVER
THE TRIBE WAS GROWING.
BACK IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT,
BABY.
Jeff: HE WAS AT THE TOP OF
AN ALLIANCE OF FIVE AND HAD
BEFRIENDED EDNA AND ADDED HEAR
AS HIS PERSONAL SIX.
WHEN IT COMES TO FRIEND, CAN
NEVER HAVE TOO MANY.
AT SAVAII, OZZY'S CONTROL WAS
ERODING.
HE FEELS HE IS ENTITLED TO
OUR DEFERENCE.
Jeff: JIM APPROACHED
COCHRAN WITH A PLAN TO UNDERMINE
OZZY BY GETTING RID OF HIS
CLOSEST ALLY.
AT THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE--
BRANDON NEEDS TO FLOSS.
UPOLU NARROWLY CHEWED OUT A WIN.
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
SENDING SAVAII TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IT'S ALL ABOUT KEEPING US AS
STRONG AS POSSIBLE.
Jeff: OZZY WANTED TO
STRENGTHEN THE TRIBE BY GETTING
RID OF COCHRAN.
SORRY, MAN, HOPE YOU FET THE
SECOND CHANCE.
Jeff: BUT THE REST OF THE
TRIBE CONSPIRED TO KEEP COCHRAN
AND OZZY WAS COMPLETELY
SURPRISED BY THE RESULT.
ELYSE HEADS TOY REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
WHEN YOU'RE ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF A BLINDSIDE YOU REALIZE WHERE
THE OTHER PEOPLE ARE.
I'M PRETTY PISSED OFF.
KEITH AND WHITNEY AND MYSELF, WE
HAD A GOOD THING GOING, AND THEY
JUST WENT BEHIND MY BACK AND
VOTED SOMEONE OUT WITHOUT
TELLING ME AND MADE ME LOOK LIKE
AN IDIOL.
HOW YOU CAN TRUST SOMEBODY WHEN
THEY GO BEHIND YOUR BACK?
IT GOES AGAINST EVERYTHING AN
ALLIANCE IS SUPPOSED TO BE.
WHATEVER, IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER.
I'M DONE PLAYING THE ALLIANCE
WAY, SO I AM NOW WHAT'S CALLED A
FREE AGENT.
AND I'M PLAYING FOR MYSELF.
AND YOU GUYS CAN PLAY FOR
YOURSELVES.
IT'S YOU VERSUS US?
THE HAND WAS PLAYED.
NO, IT WASN'T.
IT WAS, TOTALLY.
THE HAND HAS BEEN PLAYED.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE
TAKING THIS SO PERSONAL.
IT WAS 97 AGAINST YOU.
IT'S AGAINST ME WHEN YOU
DON'T TELL ME SOMETHING VERY
CRUCIAL LIKE THAT.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY AGAINST ME.
GIVE ME A BREAK, OZZY.
THERE'S STUFF THAT YOU'RE
WITHHOLDING AND YOU KNOW THAT.
I'VE GOT THE IDOL.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
YOU GUYS PLAYED YOUR HAND.
I JUST PLAYED MINE.
I HAVE THE IDOL.
AND THERE'S A WHOLE OTHER SIDE
OF THIS GAME WHICH YOU GUYS ARE
FORGETTING ABOUT AND THAT'S
CALLED REDEMPTION.
IF YOU WANT TO GO THERE, JUST
LET US KNOW, MAN.
NOW EVERY LITTLE DIRTY
LAUNDRY AND EVERY LITTLE ASPECT
OF THE GAME IS STARTING TO COME
OUT.
I TOLD EVERYONE I'VE GOT THE
IDOL.
SO FROM THIS POINT ON, I'VE JUST
DECIDED SCREW IT.
I'M JUST GOING TO LET EVERYTHING
HANG OUT THERE, TRY TO GO AS FAR
AS POSSIBLE AND IF IT DOESN'T
WORK I'VE ALWAYS GOT REDEMPTION.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
I WAS PRETTY SURPRISED THAT
THEY VOTED ELYSE OUT, THE FACT
THAT THEY FELT LIKE THEY NEEDED
TO GO BEHIND MY BACK JUST
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU TRY TO BUILD
TRIBE UNITY.
I'M JUST TRYING TO BE THE
PROVIDER.
I'M JUST TRYING TO LEAD BY
EXAMPLE, BUT THEY'VE GOT TO BE
FORTHCOMING IF THEY WANT ME TO
BE PARENT OF THIS TRIBE.
AND I'M A BIG PART OF THIS
TRIBE.
THEY WANT TO WIN CHALLENGES AND
GET FATHER, THEY'VE GOT TO TRUST
ME.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE.
HE JUST WALKED UP AND SAID,
"SEE YOU LATER."
HE SHOULD BE APOLOGIZES
TODAY.
SERIOUSLY, WHAT A CHILD.
THIS IS JUST NOT-- I'VE KNOWN
HIM FOR 14 DAYS.
I'M DISAPPOINTED.
HE NEEDS TO MAN UP AND GET
OVER IT.
THE PLAN'S COMING TOGETHER
BETTER THAN I COULD HAVE EVER
DRAWN IT UP.
NOW, AS OPPOSED TO OZZY BEING
THE LEADER, HE TWHREEZ CAN ONLY
BE DESCRIBED AS A HISSEY FIT.
I KIND OF THOUGHT OZZY WOULD
MAKE UP THIS MORNING REALIZING
HE NEEDS TO APOLOGIZE TO
EVERYBODY.
THAT WASN'T THE CASE.
HE'S TAKING HIS BALL AND GOING
TO THE OTHER SIDE OF THE ISLAND,
STILL HUFFING AND PUFFING NOT
TALKING TO ANYBODY.
WE'RE 12 HOURS AFTER THE FACT
AND HE'S STILL THIS PISSY?
COME ON.
AND NOT ONLY THAT, HE REVEALED
HE HAS THE IDOL AND SAYS HE'S A
FREE AGENT.
I MEAN, THE GUY COULDN'T HAVE
MADE ANY WORSE MOVES THAN HE
DID.
IF HE WOULD HAVE NOT REACTED
SO QUICKLY AND GOT EMOTIONAL HE
WOULD HAVE REALIZED IF WE WERE
TRYING TO BLINDED SIDE HIM, THEN
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN OUT.
ABSOLUTE.
HE DOESN'T REALIZE THAT.
I DON'T KNOW IF OZZY'S TEMPER
TANTRUM IS GOING TO CONTINUE
WELL SPOT FUTURE, BUT THE LESS
PLEASANT HE IS, THE BETTER IT IS
FOR ME.
I HOPE HE CONTINUES BOOING A CRY
BABY BECAUSE IT'S GREAT FOR ME.
IN ALL SERIOUSNESS, HE'S
BEHAVING LIKE A STUPID BITCH.
WOW!
THAT LOOKS COOL!
IT LOOKS AWESOME.
THAT'S GOOD.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
THERE'S PLENTY OF STUFF TO EAT.
I'M GOT THE IMMUNITY IDOL, SOY
I'M IN A GOOD SPOT IN THIS
TRIBE.
THE PEOPLE THAT KNOW ABOUT THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL ARE,
OBVIOUSLY, MYSELF, SOPHIE, AND
ALBERT.
IT'S SOMETHING I STRUGGLE WITH
BECAUSE I LIKE TO HAVE ALL THE
CARDS ON THE TABLE.
UNFORTUNATELY, BRANDON IS A
LOOSE CANNON AND HE MIGHT TELL
ANYBODY.
I KNOW HE WILL FEEL BETRAYED AT
SOME POINT IN TIME BUT THAT'S
DOWN THE ROAD.
JEFF TOLD US THAT THERE WAS
GOING TO BE A CLUE TO THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL IN OUR CAMP BUT
NOBODY FOUND IT.
IT IS VERY IMPORTANT FOR TO US
FIND THAT CLUE BECAUSE IT MEANS
ALMOST THE GAME IN THE MERGE.
SO I HAD A CRAZY IDEA MAYBE IT'S
IN THIS WEIRD-LOOKING TREE.
I WAS DIGGING IN THERE, LOOKING
AROUND.
SURE ENOUGH, IT WAS STUCK INSIDE
THE TREE.
HAVING A LITTLE DEJA VU RIGHT
NOW, JUST IMAGINING RUSSELL
COMING OUT HERE AND FINDING IT.
IT'S JUST CRAZY THEY FOUND IT.
LOOK AT YOU!
COME ON, MAN.
HOW DID YOU FIND IT?
RIGHT THERE.
I HAD A FEELING IT WAS UNDER THE
WEIRD TREE.
YOU KNOW, BRANDON, HE'S A
HANTZ.
HE'S GOT THE NOSE AND THE
BLOODHOUND SCENT FOR THE IDOL SO
HE IMMEDIATELY WALKS OVER TO A
TREE AND STARTS DIGGING AND
LO AND BEHOLD, THERE'S THE THIRD
CLUE.
"IT'S DEFINITELY NEAR THE
JUNGLE, SOMEWHERE BY THE BEACH."
I HAVE THE IDOL IN MY
POSSESSION.
BRANDON DOESN'T KNOW IT.
THE THING IS, I TALKED TO
BRANDON ABOUT PLAYING THIS GAME
AS CHRISTIAN MEN AND WE ARE
GOING TO DO THAT, BUT IS
WITHHOLDING INFORMATION LYING?
IT'S A GRAY AREA.
IF WE CAN'T FIND IT HERE, ONE
HOUR.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE AN ANIMAL!
I SEE GENETIC TRAITS GOING ON
RIGHT NOW, MAN.
GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M HAVING FLASHED BACKS
RIGHT NOW, MAN!
THE DETERMINATION IN YOUR WALK!
DUDE, HE'S RUSSELL HANTZ'S
NEPHEW.
DO YOU SEE IT, TOO?
JUST LIKE RUSSELL.
BEHIND A WALL OF ROOTS.
BEHIND.
DUDE, HE'S CRAZY RIGHT NOW.
HE'S GONNA TEAR THIS WHOLE
THING DOWN UNTIL HE FIND IT.
IF I WERE IN YOUR SHOES, MAN, I
DON'T THINK I'D FEEL COMFORTABLE
TELLING HIM RIGHT NOW.
HE'S SO EMOTIONAL IF HE THINKS
WE'RE 1% DISHONEST WITH HIM,
HE'D FLY OFF THE HANDLE.
BRANDON IS CLIMBING UP TREES.
IT KIND OF BREAKS MY HEART
KNOWING HE'S ON A WILD GOOSE
CHASE.
HE'S NEVER GOING TO FIND
ANYTHING.
HE MIGHT NOT BE THE SHARPEST
TOOL IN THE SHED BUT HE'LL
FIGURE OUT, WAIT, SOMEBODY
ALREADY HAS THE IDOL.
I DON'T THINK SO.
I WANT TO PLAY THIS GAME
COMPLETELY HONORABLY.
BUT NOW, THE WAY THAT I'M
WATCHING BRANDON GOING SEARCH
FOR THAT IDOL, HE LOOKS LIKE
RUSSELL.
I'M HAVING FLASHBACKS.
WHEN I SEE SOMETHING THAT REMIND
ME OF SOME HORRIBLE NIGHTMARES
THAT I LIVED THROUGH ON "HERE
EXPOSE VILLAINS" IT SCARES ME.
IT SCARES THE HECK OUT OF ME.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE CHEM PETTERS FOR TODAY'S
DUEL.
CHRISTINE WILL BATTLE AGAINST
ELYSE, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
BOTH TRIBES HAVE SENT TRIBE
MEMBERS TO WITNESS TODAY'S DUEL.
SOPHIE AND RICK AND OZZY AND
KEITH.
ELYSE, IT'S A BIG DEPARTURE,
ISN'T IT, TO BE IN THE GAME ONE
DAY AND THEN OUT HERE FIGHTING
FOR YOUR LIFE THE OTHER, AND
HAVING SOME OF THE PEOPLE WHO
VOTED YOU OUT RIGHT HERE
WATCHING.
YEAH, IT'S BITTERSWEET
BECAUSE YOU WANT TO BELIEVE THAT
THE PEOPLE YOU SPENT SO MUCH
TIME WITH THAT THEY ARE ROOTING
FOR YOU AND THEY WANT YOU BACK,
BUT, I MEAN, YOU CAN'T FORGET
THAT THEY ARE THE ONES THAT
DECIDED THAT IT WAS YOUR TIME TO
GO.
Jeff: CHRISTINE, REDEMPTION
ISLAND REALLY HAS BECOME YOUR
HOME.
MORE DAYS ON REDEMPTION THAN IN
THE GAME.
YES, IT HAS BECOME MY HOME,
UNFORTUNATELY.
Jeff: UNFORTUNATELY?
IT'S JUST HARD.
YOU KNOW, THAT I APPEAR TO BE
STRONG-- I MEAN, I AM, BUT
REDEMPTION ISLAND CAN-- CAN
BREAK YOU.
IT SUCKS.
Jeff: AND YET YOU ARE
THRIVING OUT HERE.
YOU HAVE WON THREE DUELS.
READY TO GIVE ANOTHER GO?
I'M READY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FOR
TODAY'S DUEL, YOU'RE GOING TO
PLAY A "SURVIVOR" VERSION OF
SHUFFLE BOARD.
IN THIS VERSION, YOU WILL EACH
HAVE FOUR PUCKS ON THE BOARD.
YOUR GOAL-- KNOCK OFF THE OTHER
PERSON'S PUCK BEFORE THEY KNOCK
OFF YOURS.
LAST PERSON WITH A PUCK LEFT ON
THE BOARD STAYS ALIVE AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THE LOSER IS OUT OF THIS GAME
FOR GOOD.
THIS IS IT, ONE SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
ELYSE WON ROCK, PAPER, SCISSOR.
WANTS CHRISTINE TO GO FIRST.
CHRISTINE, YOU'RE UP.
TRYING TO KNOCK OFF ALL FOUR OF
ELYSE'S PUCKS BEFORE SHE KNOCKS
OFF YOURS.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: CHRISTINE WITH THE
FIRST SHOT.
GOOSE EGG.
SHE'S TIRED.
NOTHING.
Jeff: A LITTLE BIT OF A
LEARNING CURVE.
CHRISTINE BREAKS IT UP A LITTLE
BIT.
GO, CHRISTINE.
YOU CAN DO IT.
YEAH?
CATCH THAT?
YEAH.
Jeff: ELYSE WITH A NICE
HIT, ALMOST KNOCKS IT OFF.
DAMN IT.
Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE MANAGED
TO PUT BOTH GROUPS OF PUCKS ON
EITHER SIDE OF THE BOARD.
CHRISTINE TRYING TO GET ON THE
BOARD RIGHT HERE.
AND SHE DOES, KNOCKING OFF THE
FIRST ELYSE PUCK.
ELYSE WOULD LIKE TO GET ON THE
BOARD HERE AND TIE IT UP.
AND SHE DOES.
1-1.
YOU EACH HAVE THREE PUCKS LEFT.
CHRISTINE KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER
ELYSE PUCK, LEAVING ELYSE ONLY
TWO PUCKS
AND INSTEAD, ELYSE KNOCKS OFF
ONE OF HUR OWN PUCKS, LEAVING
HER ONLY ONE PUCK LEFT.
CHRISTINE CAN WIN THE DUEL WITH
THIS SHOT TO STAY ALIVE ON
REDEMPTION.
Jeff: THAT COULD DO IT.
OH!
JUST MISSES.
ELYSE HAS GOT TO GET ON THE
BOARD.
OPPORTUNITY AFTER OPPORTUNITY.
AND SHE DOES.
ELYSE KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER
CHRISTINE PUCK.
CHRISTINE IS NOW DOWN TO TWO.
ELYSE WITH ONE.
CHRISTINE GETS ELYSE'S PUCK BACK
OUT WHERE SHE CAN KNOCK IT IN.
ELYSE KNOWS SHE'S GOT TO GET
SOMETHING GOING, GOT TO BE
AGGRESSIVE.
SHE'S GOT A SHOT DOWN THE LINE,
AND SHE GETS IT, AND WE ARE
TIED.
ELYSE AND CHRISTINE BOTH WITH
ONE PUCK LEFT ON THE BOARD.
THIS COULD BE IT.
CHRISTINE COULD WIN IT RIGHT
HERE, HER FOURTH DUEL.
CHRISTINE WINS HER FOURTH DUEL
AND STAYS ALIVE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
( APPLAUSE )
SO, ELYSE, YOU LASTED 15 DAYS.
WHAT DO YOU TAKE AWAY FROM THIS?
I THINK FOR ME, I TAKE A
SENSE OF ACCOMPLISHMENT, BECAUSE
I GAVE MY ALL.
I-- I DID.
AND I NEVER WOULD HAVE KNOWN
THEY COULD PUSH MYSELF SO FAR
HAD I NOT COME OUT HERE.
I'M STRONGER THAN I THINK I AM.
Jeff: ELYSE, YOUR ADVENTURE
HAS COME TO AN END.
IT IS TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE FIRE.
SEE YOU, ELYSE.
CHRISTINE, FOUR DUELS, FOUR
WINS.
YOU ARE STILL ON YOUR QUEST FOR
THE MILLION DOLLARS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND, LIKE IT OR
NOT, HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
THANK YOU.
CHRISTINE, STAY TOUGH.
Jeff: SOPHIE, RICK, OZZY,
CEEGTHS, YOU GUYS CAN HEAD BACK.
CHRISTINE, IF SHE COMES BACK,
I THINK SHE WOULD FLIP IN A
HURRY.
I'LL GUARANTEE YOU SHE'S GOING
TO HAVE FIRE IN HER EYES.
SHE'S GOING TO COME BACK
SMOKING, READY TO KILL US.
YEAH.
I MEAN, SHE'S SO BITTER.
IF SHE DOES COME BARK THOUGH-- I
DON'T THINK THERE'S A SHOT IN
HELL.
AT THE DUEL, CHRISTINE WAS
REALLY PISSED OFF, SO I THINK NO
MATTER WHAT SHE SAID IF SHE
COMES BACK IN THE GAME SHE WILL
NEVER BE WITH US.
SHE LOOKED AT ME AND GOES
LIKE THIS.
REALLY?
SHE'S JUST SO NEGATIVE.
SHE HAS NO ALLEGIANCE TO US.
I THINK CHRISTINE WOULD BE THE
WORST PERSON TO COME BACK FROM
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THERE'S A COCONUT RIGHT
THERE!
OH, YOU FOUND SOME?
FOUND ONE.
EDNA, I LOVE YOU!
EVER SINCE BRANDON TOLD ME I
WASN'T REALLY A PART OF THE
ALLIANCE OF SIX, I KNEW I
DEFINITELY HAD TO DO SOMETHING
SO I'VE BEEN COZYING UP NEXT TO
COACH BECAUSE I WANT TO MAKE
SURE COACH KNOWS I HAVEN'T
WAIVERS IN MY RELATIONSHIP WITH
HIM, AND I THINK IT'S WORKING.
EDNA, YOU'RE ADORABLE.
YOU'RE VERY KIND AND
GENEROUS.
THANK YOU.
MY LITTLE FRIEND OUT HERE.
YEAH.
I THINK WE WOULD BE A VERY GOOD
TEAM.
UNSUSPECTING TEAM.
WE'RE DEFINITELY VIBING.
I REALLY LIKE EDNA.
I DON'T UPON, IT'S JUST WEIRD.
YOU PICK UP WITH CERTAIN PEOPLE
AROUND HERE AND YOU JUST FEEL
COMFORTABLE AND I REALLY FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH EDNA.
SHE'S THE ONE PERSON OUT HERE
THEY THINK WOULD LAY HER
"SURVIVOR" LIFE DOWN FOR ME.
SO TO VOTE HER OFF BEFORE
MIKAYLA, WHO IS NOT PART OF THE
SIX, THAT WOULD BE CRAZY.
I TOLD YOU I'D HAVE YOUR BACK.
MIKAYLA IS THE NEXT TO GO.
YOU'RE SAFE.
I APPRECIATE IT.
COACH IS TELLING ME THAT I'M
SAFE, AT LEAST FOR A WHILE
LONGER SO I FEEL A LITTLE BIT
MORE REASSURED.
HE COULD BE LYING TO ME, BUT
RIGHT NOW I FEEL REASSURED.
WE'RE IN A GREAT SPOT.
I'LL JUST TELL YOU THAT RIGHT
NOW, CHAMP.
YUP.
I'M NOT WORRIED AT ALL.
ARE YOU READY FOR ANYTHING IN
THIS GAME?
OF COURSE.
ARE YOU READY TO FOLLOW ME
INTO BATTLE?
YES, EVEN IF IT GETS UGLY.
I FELT LIKE AFTER TRIBAL
COUNCIL, I REALLY NEEDED TO TAKE
A STAND, SO I HAD MY LITTLE
TEMPER TANTRUM, BUT I REALLY
MADE A MISTAKE.
I STILL WANT TO TRY AND MAKE
SOMETHING HAPPEN WITH THIS TRIBE
BECAUSE WE'VE GOT TO HAVE SOME
PEOPLE THAT YOU TRUST IF YOU
WANT TO MAKE IT TO THE END.
WHAT CAN WE DO FROM HERE?
I MEAN, I STILL THINK YOU AND
I CAN TAKE IT.
I DO, TOO.
I'M WILLING TO LOOK PAST IT.
I KNOW THAT YOU DIDN'T MEAN
ANYTHING REALLY BY IT.
I THINK, YOU KNOW, WHEN
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY COMES, YOU
AND I CAN KICK BUTT, AND WHOEVER
WE WANT TO GO TO THE END, WE CAN
TAKE TO THE END HUNDRED PERCENT.
I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE
TOLD THEM ABOUT THE IDOL.
I KNOW.
OZZY SETTLED DOWN A LOT.
I THINK HE KNOWS TO GET FARTHER
IN THIS GAME, HEY NEEDS THE REST
OF US AND WE NEED HIM.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING A JERK
LAST NIGHT.
I BASICALLY WANT TO DO WHATEVER
I CAN TO REUNIFY WITH YOU GUYS.
THAT WAS MY BIG REASON FOR
TELLING YOU THEY HAVE THE IDOL
BECAUSE AT THIS POINT I'D RATHER
TRY AND BE TIGHT WITH YOU GUYS
THAN BE BY MYSELF.
OZZY FINALLY REALIZES HE'S
GOT NOWHERE TO GO.
HIS WHOLE SPEECH AFTER TRIBAL
COUNCIL ABOUT BEING A FREE
AGENT.
FREE AGENT FOR WHO?
HE'S GOT NOWHERE TO GO EXCEPT
FOR US.
I LIKE HAVING OZZY ON MY SIDE.
OZZY HELPS ME WIN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES BEFORE THE MERGE.
AFTER THE MERGE HE'S A BIGGER
TARGET THAN ME.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE THAT I
COULD WANT FROM SOMEBODY ON MY
TEAM.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, EDNA, I'LL
TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
RACE TO ASSEMBLE A WHEEL BARROW.
YOU WILL THEN PUSH IT THROUGH A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES, STOPPING
ALONG THE WAY TO COLLECT TWO
LOADS OF COCONUT.
YOU WILL DUMP THE MARTHA COAKLEY
NUTS INTO A TROUGH.
THE REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS WILL
USE THE SLING SHOTS TO FIRE
COCONUTS AT TARGETS.
FIRST TRIBE TO KNOCK DOWN ALL
THEIR TARGETS WINS IMMUNITY, IS
SAFE FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNING TRIBE
EARNS REWARD.
YOU WILL LEAVE HERE AND BE TAKEN
TO A PLACE CALLED THE SLIDING
ROCKS.
IT IS A NATURAL WATER SLIDE.
YOU'LL HAVE AN AFTERNOON OF FUN
IN THE WATER AND ENJOY A NICE
PICNIC LUNCH.
YEAH!
Jeff: COACH IS ALREADY
MEDITATING ABOUT IT.
ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: WHEN YOU RETURN BACK
TO CAMP, THE WINNING TRIBE WILL
HAVE ANOTHER HIDDEN CLUE TO THE
LOCATION OF AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
UPOLU, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
MEMBER, SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
WE'RE GOING TO SIT EDNA OUT.
Jeff: EDNA, TAKE A SPOT ON
THE SIT-OUT BENCH.
THE REST OF YOU, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU HAVE TO ASSEMBLE A
"SURVIVOR" WHEEL BARROW.
ONCE YOU HAVE IT, FLIP IT, AND
GET OUT ON THE COURSE.
SAVAII AND UPOLU AT THE SAME
TIME FLIP THEIR WHEEL BARROWS.
SAVAII BLOWS IT!
OZZY RUN INTIS POST.
UPOLU HAS AN EARLY LEAD.
DAWN AND OZZY HAVING TROUBLE
WORKING TOGETHER.
SOMETHING AS SIMPLE AS
MANEUVERING A WHEEL BARROW
PROVING DIFFICULT FOR SAVAII.
UPOLU HAS THEIR FIRST BARREL OF
COCONUTS.
GOOD JOB!
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: RICK AND BRANDON
WORKING THAT BARREL TOGETHER
WELL.
SAVAII HAS THEIR FIRST BATCH OF
COCONUTS.
AS YOU-- OZZY AND DAWN STILL
STRUGGLING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
USE THIS TOGETHER.
PUSH IT, GUYS!
ON, YOU GOT THIS!
IN THE MIDDLE, BRANDON.
Jeff: SAVAII STILL HAVING
TROUBLE, LOSING MORE TIME NOW.
UPOLU CONTINUES TO WORK WELL
TOGETHER.
THEY HAVE THEIR SECOND BATCH OF
COCONUTS.
GOOD JOB, GUYS, GOOD JOB.
Jeff: GOT TO GET THEM IN
THE TROUGH.
ALL RIGHT, NEXT THREE IN.
YOU THREE ARE DONE.
GOOD WORK BY UPOLU.
THEY HAVE A BIG HEAD START NOW.
ALBERT, COACH, MIKAYLA NOW HAVE
TO TAKE THE WHEEL BARROW APART
AND BUILD A SLINGSHOT.
AS YOUY AND COCHRAN WORKING ON
THE KNOTS, AND IT IS TAKING A
LONG TIME TO GET THEIR SECOND
BATCH OF COCONUTS.
UPOLU IS ALREADY FIRING SHOT.
SAVAII HAS LOST A LOT OF TIME IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
COCHRAN!
HELP US!
PUSH!
EVERYTHING, FLIP!
Jeff: SAVAII CANNOT EVEN
GET THEIR COCONUTS IN THE
TROUGH.
ALBERT KNOCKS DOWN THE FIRST
TARGET FOR UPOLU.
SAVAII NOW TAKING THEIR WHEEL
BARROW APART.
UPOLU LEADS ONE-ZIP.
THEY'VE HAD A LOT OF TIME TO
PRACTICE.
SAVAII FINALLY HAS THEIR
SLINGSHOT TOGETHER.
JIM FIRES THE FIRST ONE AND
MISSES.
NO MORE MIKAYLA.
SHE'S NOT EVEN GETTING IT OFF
THE TARGET, JUST YOU AND I.
Jeff: THERE ARE SIX
TARGETS.
KEITH SCORES FOR SAVAII, WE ARE
TIED 1-1.
MIKAYLA GOING ONE HANDED DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE WORKING.
MIKAYLA, YOU WANT TO REST FOR
A WHILE?
NO, I'M NOT TIRED.
Jeff: ALBERT SCORES FOR
UPOLU.
UPOLU LEADS 21.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET TO SIX.
MIKAYLA STILL USING ONE HAND.
A LITTLE HIGHER MIKAYLA.
MIKAYLA, YOU WANT TO SIT OUT.
COACH, I GOT IT.
Jeff: JIM KNOCKS DOWN THE
SECOND TARGET FOR SAVAII.
WE ARE TIED NOW.
ALBERT KNOCKS DOWN THE THIRD
TARGET FOR UPOLU.
UPOLU BACK IN THE LEAD.
UPOLU HAS KNOCKED DOWN THREE.
SAVAII HAS KNOCKED DOWN TWO.
SAVAII KNOCKS DOWN THEIR THIRD
TARGET.
WE ARE TIED AGAIN.
GO MIKAYLA, GO!
Jeff: THERE ARE SIX TARGETS
TOTAL.
IT IS 3-3.
ICA VIE MAKING A HUGE COMEBACK.
JIM KNOCKS DOWN THE FOURTH
TARGET FOR SAVAII.
SAVAII NOW IN THE LEAD.
KEITH WITH THE FIFTH TARGET FOR
SAVAII.
THEY HAVE ONLY ONE TARGET LEFT.
YOU GOT THIS, JIM.
IT'S OW, JIM.
Jeff: JIM COULD WIN IT
RIGHT HERE.
YOU GOT IT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
Jeff: AND HE DOES!
SAVAII WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
WAY TO GO, BABY!
WE NEEDED THAT SO BAD.
Jeff: SAVAII, NICE WIN.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: NO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM THIS
TRIBE.
YES!
Jeff: IN ADDITION YOU WILL
LEAVE FROM HERE AND BE TAKEN TO
THE SLIDING ROCKS.
YES!
Jeff: A LITTLE BREAK FROM
THE GAME AND A NICE PICNIC
LUNCH.
OH, YEAH N-
Jeff: WHEN YOU GET BACK TO
CAMP ANOTHER HIDDEN CLUE TO THE
LOCATION OF THE IDOL.
CONGRATS, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
OUT, HAVE A GOOD TIME.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: WELL EARNED.
UPOLU, YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO
FIGURE OUT WHO'S GOING HOME.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT, SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK.
IT'S MIKAYLA'S FAULT WE LOST.
I GAVE HER DIRECTION IN THE
CHALLENGE TODAY AND SHE WOULDN'T
TAKE IT.
IF I'M GOING TO COACH THIS TEAM
I NEED FOR PEOPLE IN THE HEAT OF
BATTLE TO LISTEN TO ME.
SHE'S A PROBLEM.
MIKAYLA SHOULD GO HOME.
OH!
SWEET, SWEET VICTORY.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THICK ABOUT
THAT CHALLENGE, WE JUST HAVE TO
STAY CALM.
ALL RIGHT.
EVEN THOUGH IT LOOKED LIKE WE
WERE BEHIND, WE CAME BACK.
GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
ONE, TWO, THREE-- SAVAII!
TO WIN IMMUNITY AND REWARD
COULD NOT HAVE COME AT A BETTER
TIME.
WE WERE COMING OFF LOTS OF HURT
FEELINGS AND LOTS OF DRAMA, SO
WINNING WAS THE BEST FEELING.
SANDWICHES GALORE.
DO IT.
SANDWICHES, I'M GOING TO DIE.
CHEERS.
SAVAII SIX TO THE END, MAN.
HAVING A REWARD LIKE THIS
REALLY BROUGHT US ALL BACK
TOGETHER AND IT REALLY MADE ME
WANT SOMEBODY FROM THIS TRIBE TO
WIN THE MILLION.
IT'S I DON'T CARE IF IT'S ME-- I
DO CARE IF IT'S ME.
I WANT IT TO BE ME.
BUT IF IT'S NOT ME I DO HOPE
IT'S SOMEONE ELSE FROM MY TRIBE.
THAT WAS CRAZY!
DO YOU AGREE?
I'M NOT PHYSICALLY OR
EMOTIONALLY CAPABLE OF DOING
THAT.
YOU'RE NOT A WATER PERSON?
NOT REALLY.
I'M A SPARKLING WATER PERSON.
YOU KNOW, I'M GENERALLY NOT THAT
AGILE, SO SLIDING DOWN THESE
MOSSY ROCKS IS DEFINITELY
OUTSIDE MY COMFORT ZONE, BUT I
GOT INTO IT TODAY BECAUSE THERE
IS ALWAYS THIS KIND OF BOUNDARY
BETWEEN ME AND NATURE AND I HAD
TO STRIP IT OFF.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN DO IT.
COME ON, COCHRAN.
BE CAREFUL.
WHOOO!
YOU OKAY?
WAY TO GO!
( APPLAUSE )
INCOMING!
YEAH, BABY.
I LOVE IT!
WE WIN TOGETHER, WE LOSE
TOGETHER.
NONE OF THAT.
NONE OF THIS INDIVIDUAL I DID
THIS, BLAH BLARKS, BLAH.
WE LOST AS A TEAM.
WE LOST THE CHALLENGE AND IT
SUCKS.
NOW WE'VE GOT TO COME BACK TO
CAMP AND WE'VE GOT TO DO THE
DIRTY WORK.
WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT ARE WE
GOING TO VOTE OFF MIKAYLA OR
EDNA?
NEITHER ONE OF THEM WAS PART OF
THE ORIGINAL FIVE BUT MIKAYLA
WASN'T COACHABLE IN THE
CHALLENGE.
SHE DOESN'T FOLLOW ORDERS SO
SHE'S GOING HOME TONIGHT.
COACH AND BRANDON ARE GOING TO
TRY TO GET YOU BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO LET THAT HAPPEN.
WHY?
TRUST ME, THERE'S NOTHING TO
WORRY ABOUT.
I CAN GET COACH TO LISTEN TO ME.
SO WE LOST THE CHALLENGE.
NOW AL TOLD ME THAT COACH IS
SKEPTICAL ABOUT ME, AND IT JUST
MAKES ME LAUGH BECAUSE ALL THESE
PEOPLE ARE ABOUT STRENGTH, AND
YOU'RE REALLY THROWING MY NAME
UP AGAIN.
THE GIRL WHO IS HALF MY SIZE,
ALMOST DOUBLE MY AGE, YOU HAVE
TO BE KIDDING ME.
COACH WILL DEFINITELY GO WITH
ME.
IT'S 100% CERTAIN.
IT SUCKS, BUT I DEFINITELY DO
TRUST AL, AND WHEN IT COMES DOWN
TO IT, HOPEFULLY HE'LL TRUST IN
ME.
LISTEN, GUYS, I KNOW THAT
EDNA WAS BROUGHT IN AS THE SIXTH
PERSON, BUT EDNA HAS ZERO
CHALLENGE VALUES, ZERO.
WELL, THAT'S WHY WE HAD EDNA
SIT OUT TODAY.
THAT'S REASON WE SAT HER OUT
TO BEGIN WITH AND IF WE LOSE
THIS NEXT ONE, WE'RE IN A
TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE SPOT.
IF I HAD TO DO A "SURVIVOR"
DRAFT AND HAD EDNA AND MIKAYLA
NEXT TO EACH OTHER, IT'S A NO
BRAINER.
I'D GO WITH MIKAYLA.
EDNA IS A SHARP PLAYER WHO IS
GOING TO BE TACTICAL AND THAT'S
WAY TOO DANGEROUS.
MY FEAR IS THIS-- SHE'S SMART
ENOUGH TO KNOW SHE'S THE SIXTH
PERSON.
OH, YEAH, SHE'S BY FAR SMART
ENOUGH TO KNOW THAT.
AND SOMEONE WHO KNOWS THEY'RE
THE SIXTH PERSON IS GOING TO
MAYBE REACT DESPERATELY WHEN WE
GET TO A MERGE.
EDNA HAS BEEN BUSTING HER
ASS FOR US AND I DON'T KNOW IF
SHE'S GOING IN THE BACK OF HER
MIND YOU LAZY, NO GOOD PUKES.
ARE YOU COMFORTABLE WITH THAT
DECISION?
I THINK IT'S THE BEST FOR US
FIVE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING, SOPHIE.
WE'RE ALL CONVINCED NAIS
GOING HOME BUT WE NEED TO
CONVINCE BRANDON AND COACH OF
THAT.
HONESTLY, THE WAY WE CAME
TOGETHER ON DAY TWO WAS REAL AND
LEGITIMATE.
AND THE WAY I FEEL EDNA WAS
BROUGHT INTO THAT GROUP, IT
WASN'T AS AUTHENTIC.
I UNDERSTAND.
AND, HONESTLY, IF I CAN CHANGE
BACK TIME, HONESTLY, I WOULD NOT
VOTE MIKAYLA OFF THIS TRIBE.
I'M UNEASY ABOUT EDNA.
SHE'S GOT THIS LOOK ON HER FACE
LIKE SHE'S PLAYING PEOPLE, AND I
DON'T LIKE IT.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
I'M STARTING TO TRUST MIKAYLA
MORE BECAUSE EDNA IS JUST--
SHE'S ACTING TOO, TOO SWEET TO
NOT BE PLAYING US.
I DON'T KNOW IF EDNA IS FULL OF
ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE'S DOING.
BUT I'M STARTING TO NOT TRUST
HER.
BUT I WANT TO BE A RADICAL FOR
GOD WHEN IT COMES TO DOING
RIGHT, DOING GOOD, MAN.
I WOULD RATHER VOTE EDNA OUT OF
THIS TRIBE TODAY BUT I'M NOT
GOING TO, BECAUSE I AM MY WORD.
EVERYONE AT ONE POINT IN TIME
SAID, HEY, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
EDNA FOR OUR SIXTH.
AND I'M GOING TO STICK TO MY
WORD IF IT COSTS ME THE GAME.
I PRAY YOU GUYS RESPECT THAT.
BRENDAN ACTUALLY WANTS EDNA
TO LEAVE.
HE LIKES MIKAYLA BETTER NOW.
HE'S CHANGED HIS MIND.
SHE'S NO LONGER THE WHORE OF THE
TRIBE, BUT HE'S STILL GOING TO
VOTE HER OUT.
I DON'T GET IT.
HE IS NUTS, ABSOLUTELY NUTS.
THIS SUCKS.
BRANDON IS THE KIND OF GUY THAT,
UNFORTUNATELY, WE CAN'T TALK
STRATEGY WITH.
YOU TALK MORE THAN FIVE MINUTES
OF STRATEGY WITH HIM HE STARTS
GRABBING HIS HEAD AND IS ABOUT
TO CRY.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU RIGHT NOW,
I THINK RIGHT NOW AT THIS STAGE
KEEPING EDNA IS A MISTAKE.
I THINK THE VALUE EDNA BRINGS TO
CHALLENGES IS NOTHING.
I LOVE EDNA, DUDE, BUT NEXT
CHALLENGE IS MAKE OR BREAK.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU RIGHT
NOW FROM ONE COACH TO ANOTHER, I
LOST THE CHALLENGE TODAY.
YOU DEPARTMENT LOSE THE
CHALLENGE.
LISTEN, NO, I DID.
BECAUSE NOBODY LISTENED TO ME
TODAY.
I TOLD MIKAYLA STOP SHOOTING.
SHE'S LIKE I GOT THIS.
SHE DIDN'T GET A THING.
IF I HAD TOLD EDNA, STOP IT.
SHE WOULD HAVE STOPPED.
MIKAYLA HAS NOT WON ANYTHING FOR
US.
EDNA, IF YOU WERE TATOLL HER AT
THE MERGE, "EDNA,IMENT TO FOLLOW
OZZY WHEN HAD HE TAKES A
( BLEEP ) AND WIPE IT FOR HIM."
I THINK SHE'S PLAYING US WHEN
IT COMES TO LOYALTY.
ALBERT, I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT
NOW I'D RATHER TAKE EDNA INTO
BATTLE THAN MIKAYLA.
THE REASON COACH WANTS TO
KEEP EDNA IS COACH FEELS EDNA IS
DIRECTLY IN HIS POCKET.
HE THINKS SHE'S GOING TO LISTEN
TO EVERYTHING HE SAYS AND FOLLOW
HIM BLINDLY TO THE END.
MY CAP IS OFF TO COACH FOR
HAVING A LITTLE BIT OF STRATEGY
IN THIS, BUT REALISTICALLY,
KEEPING EDIA AROUND IS A BAD
PLAY FOR US WINNING THE NEXT
CHALLENGE AND IT'S A BAD PLAY
FOR ME IN MY END GAME.
I JUST WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
OH, YEAH.
MAN TO MAN.
I FEEL LIKE THINGS ARE TRYING TO
BE A LITTLE BIT RAILROADED RIGHT
NOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
NUMBER ONE IS GETTING TO THE
MERGE WITH NUMBERS.
NUMBER TWO IS HAVING SOMEBODY
YOU CAN TRUST THROUGH THICK AND
THIN.
EDNA IS LOYAL.
ALBERT AND SOPHIE MIGHT THINK
EDNA IS GOING HOME BUT I'M GOING
TO TELL YOU RIGHT NOW IF I HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT THAT'S
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
ALBERT SAYS SHE'S PLAYING US BUT
EDNA WILL DO WHAT SHE'S TOLD.
I WANT TO BE FORTUNE UNIFIED AS
THE FIVE OF US AND IF YOU CAN ME
WHAT MY GUT FEELING IS, GET RID
OF MIKAYLA.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING TO
SEND EDNA HOME BUT I TALKED WITH
COACH AND HE WANTS TO VOTE FOR
MIKAYLA.
COWBOY, I WANT TO TELL YOU
RIGHT NOW, MAN, THE VOTE'S IN
YOUR HANDS 100%.
I DON'T THINK ME AND SOVIET
REGOING TO AGREE WITH COACH AND
BRANDON.
IT'S 3-3 RIGHT NOW AND YOU'RE
SITTING IN THE MIDDLE.
ALL THAT DOES IS PUT A BIG
OLD TARGET ON ME.
FISEND EDNA HOME I'M GOING TO
PISS OUR COACH, AND IF I SEND
MIKAYLA HOME, I'M GOING TO PISS
OFF ALBERT.
YOU'RE DAMNED IF YOU DO, DAMNED
IF YOU DON'T.
THIS SUCKS.
Jeff: SO, COACH, BIG LOSS
TODAY.
YOU GUYS HAD A CHANCE TO TAKE
THE NUMBERS ADVANTAGE AND YOU
BLEW IT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WE JUST DIDN'T REALLY COMPETE
AS A TEAM TODAY.
YOU KNOW, WE HAD A LOT OF PEOPLE
YELLING AT PEOPLE AND MIKAYLA
AND I WERE BOTH MISSES SHOTS.
I SAID, MIKAYLA, MAYBE SHU STOP
LET ALBERT DO IT.
SHE SAID NO, LET ME DO IT.
I GOT THE FEEL OF IT.
Jeff: MIKAYLA, YOUR
EXPRESSION SAYS YOU DON'T AGREE
WITH THIS AT ALL.
WELL, DURING THE GAME,
OBVIOUSLY, AL WAS HOT.
BUT THERE WAS NEVER A POINT
WHERE COACH SAID MUCALLA, LET AL
DO THE REST OF IT.
Jeff: MIKAYLA AONCE AGAIN,
YOUR TRIBE SAT YOU OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
WHAT MESSAGE DO YOU THINK YOUR
TRIBE IS SENDING YOU?
WELL, NOBODY WANTS TO BE THE
SCRANNIEST OR LAST ONE PICKED IN
SCHOOL BUT THAT'S JUST THE WAY
IT IS WITH ME.
Jeff: BRANDON IS THERE MUCH
TALK ABOUT THE MERGE AND BEING
UP OR DOWN WITH THE NUMBERS?
ABSOLUTELY.
WE HAVE TO BE UP IN NUMBERS IN
THE MERGE.
THIS NEXT CHALLENGE IS
ABSOLUTELY DETRIMENTAL TO THE
WAY THIS GAME TURNS OUT.
Jeff: THERE ARE TWO SIDES
TO THAT COIN.
ONE IS DO YOU KEEP THE PLAYER
THAT WILL HELP YOU GET TO THE
MERGE OR DO YOU KEEP THE PLAYER
WHO WILL BE LOYAL AFTER A MERGE?
YOU GOTTA GET THERE, BUT YOU
WANT TO GET THERE WITH PEOPLE
WHO ARE GOING TO BE LOYAL.
WHAT'S NUMBERS IF ONE OR TWO
PEOPLE ON YOUR TRIBE IS NOT
LOYAL?
IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
Jeff: ALBERT, WHAT IF THE
PERSON YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
BEING LOYAL IS THE SAME PERSON
WHO HELPS YOU GET TO THE MERGE
WITH NUMBERS?
IF THE ONE PERSON THAT HELPS
YOU GET TO THE MERGE ISN'T THE
MOST LOYAL, TO ME THAT'S
SOMETHING WE HAVE TO COMPROMISE
BECAUSE IN THIS GAME IT'S OF THE
UTMOST IMPORTANCE TO GET TO THE
MERGE WITH NUMBERS AND AN EDGE.
Jeff: YOU'RE SAYING CAN'T
WORRY ABOUT THE LOYALTY AFTER
THE MERGE IF YOU DON'T GET TO
THE MERGE.
RIGHT.
Jeff: SOPHIE, WHERE DO YOU
FALL ON THIS MERGE ARGUMENT?
I THINK YOU GO IN DOWN
NUMBERS IN THE MERGE IT, DOESN'T
MATTER IF EVERYBODY IS LOYAL.
IT DOESN'T.
YOU HAVE TO GO IN WITH AS MANY
AS YOU CAN AND BE AS STRONG AS
YOU CAN.
Jeff: COACH, A DIVIDED
TRIBE.
A FEW PEOPLE THINK TAKE THE BEST
TO THE MERGE.
WE'LL DOOL WITH LOYALTY LATER.
AND SOME OF THE OTHERS SAY DEAL
WITH LOYALTY RIGHT NOW.
ABSOLUTELY.
IT DOES DIVIDE THE TRIBE.
FOR ME YOU KNOW WHAT MY ANSWER
IS GOING TO BE, HONOR, LOYALTY,
INTEGRITY.
THE ONE THING THAT WORRIES ME
IS LOYALTY CAN BE FAKED.
YOU CAN'T FAKE STRENGTH.
A REALLY GOOD PERSON REQUEST CON
PEOPLE INTO BELIEVING THEY'RE
LOYAL.
IT'S HARD TO CON PEOPLE TO
BELIEVE YOU'RE REALLY GOOD,
ATHLETIC AND STRONG.
Jeff: BRANDON.
I'M REALLY TRYING TO BE QUIET
BUT I CAN'T.
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL WE WERE
TALKING LOYAL, LOYAL, LOYAL.
AND THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL WE'RE
TALKING LOYAL.
HOW COME WE'RE SPLIT?
WE ALL MADE A PACT TO HAVE SIX
PEOPLE THAT WERE GOING TO MAKE
IT AND WE WERE GOING TO STAY,
AND WE CHOSE TO KEEP EDNA.
I LOVE YOU, MIKAYLA ABUT I WANT
TO KEEP EVERYBODY TO THEIR WORD.
SO THERE SHOULD BE ONLY ONE VOTE
BEING VOTED TONIGHT.
HALF OF US ARE ON ONE SIDE, HALF
OF US ARE ON THE OTHER AND IT
CONCERNS ME.
THAT'S NOT LOYALTY.
THAT'S A HOUSE DIVIDED AND A
HOUSE DIVIDE--
THAT'S A DIFFERENCE IN
OPINION, THOUGH.
LOYALTY AND OPINIONS ARE TWO
SEPARATE IDEAS.
WE'RE NOT UNDERSTANDING, MAN.
WE CANNOT BE DIVIDED AND HAVE
LOYALTY.
VOTE ME OUT TODAY IF WE'RE GOING
TO PLAY DISLOYAL, BECAUSE MONEY
YOU CAN THROW IT IN THAT FIRE
AND IT'S GONE.
CHARACTER YOU LIVE WITH FOR THE
REST OF YOUR LIFE.
Jeff: SO, MIKAYLA, IT
SOUNDS LIKE YOU ARE IN THE
MIDDLE OF A DIVIDED TRIBE-- AT
LEAST THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
IS THAT WHAT YOU HEARD?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY, BRANDON'S
HAD SOMETHING AGAINST ME FROM
THE BEGINNING--
BECAUSE I DON'T TRUST YOU YOU
OR EDNA STRATEGICALLY IN THIS
GAME.
HONESTLY, I WANT TO KEEP MIKAYLA
HERE.
BUT BECAUSE I SAID I WOULD NOT
VOTE EDNA OUT OF THIS TRIBE, I'M
BOUND TO WHAT I SAID, PERIOD.
Jeff: BRANDON, ONE OF THE
THINGS YOU SAID WAS IF WE'RE
GOING TO PLAY A GAME THAT'S NOT
BASED ON LOYALTY, VOTE ME OUT
TONIGHT.
COACH, EXPLAIN TO BRANDON THE
DOWN SIDE OF TELLING SOMEBODY
YOU'RE GOING TO VOTE THEM OUT
BEFORE THE VOTE.
THE PROBLEM IS THERE'S A
POINT OF BEING TOO HONEST AND
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER THAT THERE
ARE SOME CARDS THAT NEED TO BE
REVEALED AND SOME CARDS THAT YOU
KEEP HIDDEN FOR A TIME.
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT YOU'RE
BEING DISLOYAL OR DISHONEST.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE
NOWADAYS, PEOPLE GET THE
MISCONCEPTION THAT WE CAN TELL A
HALF LIE OR TELL A LITTLE BIT OF
A LIE.
OH, IT'S JUST A GAME.
OH, IT'S JUST A CIGARETTE.
OH, IT'S JUST A LITTLE BIT OF
MARIJUANA.
OARING'S IT'S JUST A LITTLE BIT
BIT.
YOU KNOW THAT'S LASCIVIOUSNESS.
THERE ARE NO GRAY.
IT'S BLACK OR WHITE, PERIOD.
Jeff: WELL, AFTER TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL, THE ONLY THING I
CAN SAY WITH CERTAINTY,
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
TIME FIND OUT WHO.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
BRANDON, YOU'RE UP.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW YOU GOT
THIS FAR.
I REALLY HOPE IT'S YOU
TONIGHT OR ELSE WE'RE IN A WORLD
OF PAIN.
COME ON, COWBOY, VOTE FOR HER,
TOO.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN IDOL
AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SOY.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MIKAYLA.
EDNA.
MIKAYLA.
TWO VOTES MIKAYLA.
EDNA.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES MIKAYLA, TWO VOTES
EDNA.
MIKAYLA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES MIKAYLA, TWO
VOTES EDNA.
EDNA.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES MIKAYLA, THREE VOTES
EDNA, ONE VOTE LEFT.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC,"
MIKAYLA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
MIKAYLA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
ALL THIS TALK ABOUT LOYALTY, AND
STILL THE SPLIT VOTE.
AND THAT'S BECAUSE LOYALTY, AS
HONORABLE AS IT MAY BE, IS NOT
ALWAYS THE ANSWER.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
I DON'T WANT TO GO TO
REDEMPTION, BUT IF IT'S LIKE A
DO OUR DIE SITUATION, I WILL GO.
FATHER WE ASK FOR A
REJUVENATION OF THIS TRIBE.
IF THIS COMES A TIME BRANDON
BECOMES A LIABILITY WE HAVE TO
PUT A BULLET IN SOMEBODY'S HEAD.
JUST KEEP GOING, ALBERT!
OF.
Jeff: WE ARE NECK AND NEXT
RIGHT NOW!
TRIBAL WAS A MESS, MAN.
EVERY TIME BRANDON HAS A BLOW-UP
IT'S, LIKE, ALWAYS POINTED AT A
STRONGER WOMAN.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW EDNA
HAS MADE IT THIS FAR.
I WOULD LOVE TO DEFINITELY GET
SOME PEOPLE BACK.
I'M JUST GOING TO LAUGH IF THE
NEXT CHALLENGE IS SOMETHING
PHYSICAL.
WHAT HAPPENED?