Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": WE ARE NOW NECK AND
NECK.
IN THE BATTLE BETWEEN TWO
TRIBES, EACH WITH A LEGEND
FORMER PLAYER-- UPOLU WINS
IMMUNITY!
UPOLU, LED BY COACH, NARROWLY
WON THE FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
SO OZZY'S TRIBE, BLINDSIDED
THEIR WEAKEST PLAYER.
SEMHAR, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND SENT HER TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
MEANWHILE, AZY STRENGTHENED HIS
POSITION IN THE TRIBE BY FINDING
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THIS MIGHT BE MY TICKET TO
THE WIN.
Jeff: AND JOINING AN
ALLIANCE OF FIVE.
ME, KEITH, AZY, ALLYCE AND
WHITNEY.
Jeff: COACH BUILT HIS OWN
ALLIANCE OF FIVE AND BRANDON
FELT SO CLOSE TO COACH, THAT HE
REVEALED HIS SECRET.
HIS UNCLE IS NIGH MY NUMBER
ONE NEMESIS, RUSSELL HANTZ.
AFTER UPOLU LOST THE SECOND
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, COACH WANTED
TO GET CHRISTINE OUT.
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN WHAT
CHRISTINE SAID ON DAY ONE--
COACH IS A TEMPORARY PLAYER.
Jeff: BUT BRANDON INNATELY
DIDN'T TRUST MIKAYLA.
SO HE TOOK A PAGE FROM HIS
UNCLE'S PLAYBOOK AND SPREAD
FALSE RUMORS TO GET HER OUT.
JUST WALKED UP TO COACH AND I
LIED TO HIM.
STACEY AND CHRISTINE TOLD ME
THEY'RE VOTING OUT MIICALLIA.
Jeff: BUT AT TRIBAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BRANDON CONFESSED
TO HIS SINS.
I TOLD EVERYONE TO VOTE FOR
MIKAYLA.
Jeff: IN THE END, COACH GOT
WHAT HE WANTED.
CHRISTINE, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
AND CHRISTINE WAS SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WE'RE ONLY FIVE DAYS INTO THIS
GAME AND ALREADY THE BIGGEST
OBSTACLE FOR THIS TRIBE IS
TRUST.
16 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT?
HELLO?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
CHRISTINE.
HI.
SEMHAR.
SEMHAR?
YEAH.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED AT TRIBAL?
I THINK MY TRIBE WAS NOT READY
FOR SOMEONE WHO WANTED TO PLAY
THE GAME RIGHT OUT OF THE BOX.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH.
WHAT IS HE LIKE?
HE'S A BIG, FAT, PAIN IN THE
ASS.
REALLY?
HE THINKS HE'S KING FAROUK.
I THINK COACH JUST HAD IT OUT
FOR ME FROM THE BEGINNING AND HE
WAS GOING TO DO WHATEVER IT TOOK
TO GET ME OUT, AND HE SUCCEEDED.
AT LEAST REDEMPTION ISLAND GIVES
ME ANOTHER CHANCE TO GET BACK
INTO IT.
IT'S NOT OVER YET.
FAT LADY HAS NOT SUNG.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WE'RE ALL HERE TO SEE ANOTHER
DAY.
TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS NUTS
TONIGHT.
I DIDN'T EXPECT TO SEE, E, YOU
KNOW, BRANDON TO BE THE ONE
SAYING LET'S VOTE FOR MIKAYLA.
YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST LIKE, WOW.
I WAS THINKING WHAT DID I DO?
WHAT DID I DO?
I COULDN'T PINPOINT A THING.
BRANDON MAY SEEM LIKE HE'S JUST
THIS LITTLE COUNTRYBOY BOYBUT
HE'S STIRRING STUFF UP AND I'M
REALLY NOT HAPPY ABOUT IT.
COACH CAME OUT AND TOOK THE HEAT
OFF ME AND I HOPE IT STAYS OFF
ME.
I HAD NO IDEA.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS GOING ON.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO INTERRUPT
YOU GUYS.
NO, YOU'RE NOT INTERRUPTING.
YOU'RE NOT INTERRUPTING AT ALL,
MAN.
TRIBAL COUNCIL SUCTION SO
BAD.
I WAS ALMOST 150% SURE
MIKAYLA WAS GOING HOME.
THE PLAN BACKFIRED.
IT WAS A BLATANT LIE, AND I
REGRET EVER DOING THAT.
I CAME INTO THIS GAME NOT
WANTING TO BE LIKE MY UNCLE
RUSSELL AND HIS REPUTATION THAT
HE HAS OF BEING A VILLAIN ON
"SURVIVOR."
I WANTED TO BE A HERO.
I WANTED TO BE SOMEONE THAT YOU
COULD LOOK UP TO.
I'M GUILTY, COMPLETELY GUILTY OF
THE WAY THEY ACTED, AND I REAP
WHAT I SOW MAN.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
TREE MAIL!
TREE MAIL.
TWO PRAYERS SO FAR
HAVE BEEN VOTED OUT.
TODAY THEY WILL PLAY FOR
THEIR LIVES.
CHOOSE TWO FROM YOUR
TRIBE TO WITNESS THE
MATCH TO SEE WHOM LEAVES
AND WHO SURVIVES?
WE JUST GOT A TREE
MAIL INVITING US TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I WOULD HUMBLY REQUEST
THE TRIBEY ALLOW ME TO
GO TO THIS REDEMPTION.
I WOULD LIKE TO GO.
I WANT TO GO, TOO.
DONE.
GOOD DEAL.
I'LL GO TO THE DUEL
TODAY WITH STACEY.
THE BEST PART OF THIS
DAY WOULD BE IF
CHRISTINE LOST BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT HER AT ANY
POINT IN TIME COMING
BACK TO THE GAME.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW
BRING IN THE COMPETITORS
FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
SEMHAR WILL BATTLE
AGAINST CHRISTINE, VOTED
OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CHRISTINE, UGLY TRIBAL
ANY ANIMOSITY TOWARD THE
TWO PEOPLE THAT ARE HERE
TODAY?
COACH WADE, YOU KNOW,
HE DIDN'T LIKE ME FROM
THE BEGINNING.
I JUST ARTICULATED WHAT
EVERYONE ELSE WAS
SAYING.
Mike: YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT TELLING
HIM HE WAS GOING HOME.
RIGHT.
AND THEN HE DISLIKED
ME, AND I THINK THAT WAS
HIS OBJECTIVE, TO GET ME
OUT AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
SO I WANT TO GET BACK IN
THE GAME FOR ME.
Jeff: TELL ME ABOUT
REDEMPTION ISLAND,
SEMHAR.
YOU WERE OUT THERE FOR A
FEW NIGHTS ALL ALONE.
YEAH, REDEMPTION
ISLAND IS SCARY AND I
WAS ALONE.
I'M JUST READY TO KEEP
GOING.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT,
SHALL WE GET TO TODAY'S
DUEL?
TODAY'S DUEL WILL
REQUIRE CONCENTRATION
AND BALANCE.
ON MY GO, YOU WILL PLACE
A WOODEN TOTEM ON TOP OF
A POLE.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS YOU
WILL ADD ANOTHER SECTION
OF POLE, MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT TO KEEP
STABLE.
IF YOUR TOTEM FALLS OFF,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE DUEL
AND OUT OF THE GAME FOR
GOOD.
WINNER STAYS ALIVE AND
CONTINUES THEIR QUEST
FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS.
OKAY.
Jeff: MAKE SENSE?
THIS IS IT.
ONE SHOT, TAKE YOUR
SPOTS.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING
I WOULDN'T DO FOR THIS
MAN.
I WOULD EVEN TAKE OFF MY
CLOTHES AND GIVE HIM A
PRIVATE SHOW TO THE
TUNES OF THE SOUL
BECAUSE HE'S ALL THEY
NEED NO MORE.
I WOULD GIVE BIRTH TO 10
OF HIS CHILDREN WITHOUT
USE ANYTHING DRUGS TO
HELP EASE THE PAIN AND
THEN I WOULD GIVE HIM
ONE MORE JUST BECAUSE
OUR LOVE IS THAT INSANE.
THERE IS NOT ONE THING
THEY WOULD NOT DO FOR MY
LOVER, MY BEST, FRIEND,
MY HONEY, MY BOO.
I CAN'T WAIT TO
MEET HIM.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOOD.
Jeff: IS THAT A
LITTLE SPOKEN WORD?
DOES THAT CALM YOU?
LIKE CRAZY.
Jeff: CHRISTINE,
YOU CALM?
LET'S DO THIS DUEL.
TAKE YOUR FIRST POLE.
PLACE YOUR TOTEM ON TOP.
GET IT WHERE YOU WANT
IT.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE POLE
IN PLACE, BOTH HANDS
NEED TO BE ON THE
HANDLE.
THIS DUEL IS ON.
BE VERY CAREFUL WITH
YOUR MOVEMENTS.
IT IS ABOUT
CONCENTRATION AND
REMEMBERING WHERE THAT
CENTER POINT IS.
OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO ADD
ANOTHER SECTION OF POLE.
WATCH YOUR BALANCE, MAKE
SURE THAT IS LEVEL.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
MAKE SURE THAT TOTEM
DOESN'T FALL WHILE
YOU'RE DOING THIS.
CHRISTINE HAS HER SECOND
SECTION IN.
SEMHAR HAS HER SECOND
THE BEAUTIFUL THING
ABOUT REDEMPTION ISLAND,
IT IS A SECOND CHANCE.
THERE WOULD BE NOTHING
SWEETER THAN TO GET BACK
INTO THIS GAME.
ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME TO
ADD ANOTHER SECTION OF
POLE.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
DO NOT PANIC, AND DO NOT
LOSE IT.
IF IT FALLS WHILE YOU'RE
PUTTING ANOTHER SECTION
IN, YOU ARE OUT OF THIS
DUEL.
SEMHAR WITH A NICE
RECOVERY.
BOTH WOMEN IN GOOD
SHAPE.
BOTH WOMEN STRONG AGAIN.
KEEP FOCUSED.
DON'T DRIFT.
DON'T START THINKING
ABOUT ANYTHING.
CHRISTINE STARTING TO
WOBBLE.
THE LONGER THESE POLES
GET, THE MORE LIKELY
THEY ARE TO SWAY AT THE
TOP.
SEMHAR WITH JUST A
LITTLE BIT OF MOVEMENT.
CHRISTINE SLIPPING A
LITTLE.
SEMHAR LOSE HERSELF
TOTEM.
CHRISTINE STATES ALIVE.
AND CONTINUES HER QUEST
FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS.
SO, SEMHAR, WHAT'S THE
EMOTION?
MY TRIBE SENT ME TO
REDEMPTION, IT JUST
BROUGHT BACK A LOT OF
MEMORIES FROM MY PAST.
I'VE MOVED SO MANY TI
TIMESES, AND I AND I
HAVE FELT ABANDON SO
MANY TIMES IN MY LIFE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW
PEOPLE CAN BE SO CRUEL
AND IT'S HOW I FELT
ABOUT MY TRIBE.
Jeff: AND YET YOU
SOUGHT OUT THIS GAME.
>>Y EXACTLY.
THAT'S WHY I'M PROUD OF
MYSELF.
I NEVER GIVE UP ON
ANYTHING.
I'M SAD TO BE THE FIRST
TO GO BUT I KNOW I
PLAYED THIS FAITHFULLY
AND AS A GOOD PERSON.
Jeff: SEMHAR, YOUR
ADVENTURE HAS COME TO AN
END.
IT IS TIME FOR YOU TO
GO.
BY, SWEETIE.
BYE, LOVE.
YOU DID GOOD.
BE WELL, OKAY?
OKAY.
BE A STRONG GIRL.
THANK YOU, LOVE YOU.
BURN!
Jeff: CHRISTINE,
CONGRATULATIONS YOU HAVE
SEIZED THE MOMENT.
YOU HAVE STAYED ALIVE TO
SEE ANOTHER DAY IN THIS
GAME.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND AND AWAIT YOUR
NEXT OPPONENT.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: CONGRATS.
AS WITH ANY DUEL, WHAT
YOU DECIDE TO SHARE WITH
YOUR TRIBEMEMBERS BACK
AT CAMP IS UP TO YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK.
COACH WAS AT THE DUEL
TO SEE IF I WOULD LOSE.
HE'S JUST A DOPE.
I'M HOPING THEY PULL A
MATT AND HAVE A RUN HERE
AND THEN GET BACK IN.
I KNOW I'LL WIN.
THIS MORNING, GOD WAS
CHASTISING ME BIG TIME.
HE WAS NOT PLEASED WITH ME.
I WAS NOT PLEASED WITH ME, AND I
KNOW MY FAMILY WOULDN'T BE
PLEASED WITH ME.
I LIED BLATANTLY.
I KNEW THAT MY TRIBE WOULD
BELIEVE ME, AND I LIED TO THEM.
THEY WANTED CHRISTINE TO GO
HOME, BUT I KNEWIMENTED MIKAYLA
TO GO HOME.
THERE'S JUST CERTAIN THINGS THAT
I CAN'T ALLOW MYSELF TO CONTINUE
ON.
I DON'T WANT TO LIE ANY MORE.
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY GAMES ANY
MORE WITH THESE PEOPLE.
I REALLY WANTED TO TAKE OFF MY
SHIRT REALLY BAD.
IS EVERYBODY HERE?
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU GUYS AND
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING WAS OUT IN
THE OPEN.
UHM, MY NAME IS BRANDON HANTZ.
I'M RUSSELL HANTZ'S NEPHEW.
I'M SORRY.
ARE YOU REALLY?
WOW.
AND I'M NOT THE SAME PERSON
THAT HE IS.
I APOLOGIZE FOR THAT.
AND I ACCEPT THE CONSEQUENCES OF
WHAT I DID.
I JUST-- I'D RATHER MAKE FRIENDS
OUT HERE THAN A MILLION DOLLARS.
HE COMES OUT AND SAYS HE'S
RUSSELL'S NEPHEW.
I'M LIKE WHOA.
I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
BEHIND THIS KID.
YOU SAY YOU DON'T WANT TO LIE
BUT YOU KEEP DOING IT.
I THINK IT'S AN EASY OUT FOR
HIM.
HE DOES SOMETHING BAD AND HE'S
HEE GOES, "GUYS THAT'S NOT ME."
YOU HAVE HANTZ ON YOUR ARM.
I FEEL LIKE NOBODY NOTICED THAT.
MAYBE HE'S TRYING TO COVER
HIS TRACKS BEFORE HE MAKES THEM.
BUT I DON'T TRUST HIM.
I THINK HE'S A SNEAK.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT HIS
PROBLEM IS WITH ME.
WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE?
I'M BRANDON HANTZ.
I'M ME.
I LOVE GOD.
I LOVE JESUS CHRIST, AND I
SHOULDN'T BE ASHAMED OF THE FACT
THAT I'M A DIFFERENT PERSON THAN
MY UNCLE.
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU BEFORE
I DID IT, BUT I WAS REALLY
CONFLICTED, MAN.
HONESTY IS THE BEST POLICY,
MAN.
I COMMEND YOU FOR SAYING THAT.
I REALLY DO.
TRUST ME, I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO
BEEF WITH YOU WHATSOEVER.
THANK YOU.
BRANDON TOLD THE TRIBE THAT
HE WAS RUSSELL HANTZ'S NEPHEW.
A MISTAKE, IN MY OPINION, BUT HE
NEED TO GET IT OFF HIS CHEST
AND, YOU KNOW, THAT SHOWS
BRANDON'S AGE A LITTLE BIT.
HE LETS THINGS GET TO HIM THAT
CAN WEIGH HIM DOWN.
IT'S NOT A COOL THING, MAN.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
MANIPULATION IS MANIPULATION, NO
MATTER HOW YOU COAT IT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF I'M
MANIPULATING YOU, IF I'M NOT
MANIPULATING YOU, IF I'M
MANIPULATING EVERYBODY ELSE.
RIGHT.
BRANDON IS A VALUABLE OF THE
SENATE MY ALLIANCE.
I STILL TRUST BRANDON,
ABSOLUTELY.
BUT IT'S JUST MAYBE NOT IN WITH
BOTH FEET NOW.
I KIND OF HAD A RELAPSE OF
WHAT MY UNCLE USED TO DO AND IT
SUCKED.
BEST ONE YET, I THINK.
WE HAVE A GOOD CAMP LIFE.
WE HAVE FOOD.
WE HAVE SHELTER.
PEOPLE GET ALONG.
BUT THE REALITY IS, IN EVERY
TRIBE, THERE'S A PECKING ORDER.
I THINK THE MINORITY IS ME,
COCHRAN, AND DAWN.
ME AND DAWN FOR AGE, AND COCHRAN
BECAUSE HE JUST IS THE NERDY KID
NOBODY HUNG OUT WITH IN SCHOOL.
SORRY, JOHN.
I JUST DIDN'T CLICK WITH ANYONE
HERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
SO EVERY CHALLENGE IS IMPORTANT
TO ME.
I AM NOT SAFE AT ALL.
YEAH, BABY.
OZZY, THAT'S AWESOME.
IT'S MYSELF, KEITH, WHITNEY,
ALLYCE, AND JIM.
BUT I THINK KEITH AND I, WE
HAVE, LIKE, A SORT OF
BROTHER-TYPE THING GOING ON.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A CERTAIN
POINT WHERE I HAVE TO TRUST
SOMEBODY WITH THE KNOWLEDGE THAT
I HAVE THE IDOL, AND WHO BETTER
THAN KEITH?
I JUST THINK THAT HE'S GOING TO
BE A STRONG ALLY, AND AS FAR AS
I KNOW, HE'S REALLY TRUSTED
WORTHY.
I HAVE THE IDOL.
AW, SWEET!
LIKE I SAID, MAN, I TRUST
YOU, AND I--
I HOPE SO.
I MEAN, I TRUST YOU.
IF I DIDN'T, I WOULDN'T HAVE
SAID ANYTHING.
OSSIE FOUND IT.
YOU'RE SURE?
YUP.
100% POSITIVE?
YEAH.
HE TOLD YOU?
YUP.
I'M KIND OF SURPRISED HE TOLD
YOU.
HE HAS TO TELL ME BECAUSE IT
GIVES HIM ALL THE POWER.
RIGHT.
I'M MAD THAT OZZY HAS THE
IDOL BECAUSE IT GIVES HIM ALL
THE POWER-- OR MOST OF THE POWER
RIGHT NOW PUP KNOW, IT GIVES HIM
THE BETTER HOLDS ON THE
ALLIANCE.
SO I TOLD WHITNEY BECAUSE I WANT
HER TO TRUST ME JUST IN CASE
DOWN THE LINE SOMETHING WERE TO
HAPPEN WHERE I NEEDED NUMBERS
BECAUSE I THOUGHT OZZY MIGHT BE
MAKING A MOVE.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL THAT
HE DOESN'T KNOW THEY TOLD YOU.
RIGHT, OKAY.
AND IT'S GOT TO BE LIKE HARD.
HEY, BRANDON, YOU GOT A
MINUTE, BUD?
SO I WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU HAVE
AGAINST ME?
I-- I WANTED YOU TO GO HOME.
I THINK IT'S FUNNY.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU HAD A PROBLEM,
YOU SAY, "MIKAYLA, WHAT'S THE
DEAL?"
DID YOU COME UP TO MY FACE?
NO, YOU DID SNEAKY STUFF BEHIND
MY BACK.
ARE YOU TRYING TO MESS WITH MY
WORDS BECAUSE YOU WANT ME OUT
BECAUSE YOU DON'T LIKE ME.
THAT'S WHAT IT WAS.
IT WAS.
IT REALLY WAS.
AND I MADE THAT 19 TO EVERYBODY.
WHY DON'T YOU LIKE ME?
JUST THE ATTITUDE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY WE'RE HAVING
THE CONVERSATION BECAUSE IS
SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE STILL TRYING
TO GET THE FACT THAT I'M
APOLOGIZING TO YOU.
YOU JUST TOLD ME YOU DIDN'T
LIKE ME.
BEFORE ME DOING ANYTHING,
PEOPLE DIDN'T TRUST YOU.
MIKAYLA WAS COMING AT ME LIKE A
BULLDOG, LIKE SHE WAS GOING TO
ATTACK ME.
HEY, GUYS, CAN WE GATHER AROUND
FOR A SECOND?
BUT AS A CHRISTIAN, I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE MEEK.
I'M SUPPOSED TO TURN THE OTHER
CHEEK.
BUT I'M TELL YOU AS A MAN I
WANTED YOU OUT OF THIS GAME
REALLY BAD.
AND SHE WALKED UP TO ME THE WAY
SHE DID, I WAS VERY UPSET.
WHAT I'M TRYING TO EXPLAIN TO
HER, SHE'S WONDERING WHY I WANT
TO VOTE HER OUT, OKAY.
AND YOU MIGHT WANT TO LOOK
AROUND AND SEE WHO IS REALLY
LOYAL AND WHO IS REALLY NOT
BECAUSE IT SOUNDS LIKE TO ME YOU
DON'T HAVE MUCH OF AN ALLIANCE,
PERIOD.
ANYBODY HAS ANYTHING TO SAY?
I DON'T WANT NO MORE OF THIS
FROM EVERYBODY.
I-- JUST RESPECT THAT FROM ME.
KEEP ME OUT OF THE DRAMA.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S IT.
GOD, OH, MY GOD.
I WAS IN SO MUCH SHOCK.
WE ALL DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING AFTER
THAT.
HE SAY LOOSE CANNON AND THERE'S
A LOT OF TENSION BETWEEN BRENDAN
AND MIKAYLA INSPECT HIS BIBLICAL
TERMS HE'D PROBABLY CALL HER THE
WHORE OF BABYLON.
I THINK BRANDON RIGHT NOW, HE'S
TORN BETWEEN FOLLOWING WHATEVER
CRAZY BELIEFS HE HAS, AND YET AT
THE SAME TIME HE INHERENTLY IN
HIS BLOOD LINE IS A DEVIOUS
JERK.
I WAS TOLD BY MY POP ABY MY
DAD, DO NOT LOSE YOUR TEMPER.
AND IT'S PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
BEING ACARINE, I SHOULDN'T HAVE
LOST MY TEMPER.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
CONTROL MYSELF AND I DIDN'T.
I FAILED.
I JUST LET MY FLESH GET AHOLE OF
ME.
I MEAN, I STRUGGLE EVERY DAY.
THIS IS-- THIS IS LIKE A
CONSTANT BATTLE FOR ME--
GOOD-EVIL, GOOD-EVIL, GOOD-EVIL.
I REALLY WANT TO DO GOOD.
YOU JUST, LORD, PLEASE DON'T LET
ME SIN ANYMORE.
WHAT YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
DO IS SAY, "COME ON, LET'S JUST
LAY IT ALL OUT, SCREW YOU," AND
THEN YOU SPOOK YOUR OWN ALLIANCE
AND YOU SPEAK MIKAYLA.
THAT BASICALLY DID NOBODY ANY
GOOD.
THIS SITUATION GREATLY CONCERNS
ME.
IT IS THE EPITOME OF SNAFU.
I'M WORRIED THAT BRANDON'S
OUTBURST CAUSES UNEASINESS IN
THE TRIBE, UNEASINESS IN THE
ALLIANCE, AND WE ARE ALL HOPING
AND PRAYING THAT BRANDON HAS NO
FURTHER SUCH OUTBURSTS.
IT'S A DIFFERENT KIND OF
AGGRESSION THAN RUSSELL HAD, BUT
IT'S AN AGGRESSION NONETHELESS.
I HATE TO SAY IT, THE BUT I DO
SEE A LITTLE RUSSELL IN IN HIM.
OH, TOTALLY.
I JUST HOPE IT DOESN'T BITE US
IN THE BUTT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES.
YES!
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST--
SAVAII, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
ON MY GO, ONE PERSON FROM EACH
TRIBE WILL RACE ACROSS A
FLOATING BRIDGE CARRYING A BODY
BOARD ATTACHED TO A LONG ROPE.
ONCE YOU REACH THE PLATFORM,
YOU'LL GRAB A BAG AND HANG ON AS
THE REST OF THE TRIBE WILL CRANK
A GIANT WENCH BRINGING YOU BACK
TO SCORE.
THE REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS WILL
USE GRAPPLING HOOKS TO RETRIEVE
THEM.
INSIDE THE BAGS ARE PUZZLE
BANNERS.
YOU MUST ROLL THE BANNERS DOWN
THE FACE OF THE WALL AND ARRANGE
THEM TO FORM YOUR TRIBE FLAG.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
OH!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
YEAH!
YA!
Jeff: YOU'VE GOT COFFEE,
TEA, SUGAR, MILK, SOME
CHOCOLATE, SOME COOKIES TO GO
ALONG WITH IT.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL HAVE ANOTHER CLUE TO THE
LOCATION OF A HIDDEN IDOL,
HIDDEN AT THEIR CAMP.
WORTH PLAYING FOR.
YES!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GO, BRENDAN, GO!
Jeff: BRENDAN AND OZZY OUT
ON THE COURSE, FIRST.
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE THEM ENOUGH
SLACK OR YOU WILL SLOW THEM
DOWN.
SLOW DOWN, SLOW DOWN!
Jeff: OZZY NEEDS SOME MORE
ROPE.
IF YOU'RE NOT MANAGING YOUR
ROPE, IT'S GOING TO COST YOU.
BRANDON NOW WITH A BIT OF A
LEAD.
FEED IT!
Jeff: BRANDON HAS HIS BAG.
GO, B!
PULL, PULL!
KEEP IT UP, OZZY!
FEED THE ( BLEEP ) ROPE!
Jeff: OZZY CANNOT RUN, HE
DOESN'T HAVE ANY ROPE.
BRANDON HEADING BACK, GETTING A
NICE RIDE.
OZZY HAS HIS BAG.
GO!
Jeff: HIS TRIBE NOW
CRANKING PAPA BEAR STRUGGLING TO
KEEP UP.
BRANDON'S BACK.
OZZY COMING BACK.
UPOLU WITH A BIT OF A LEAD.
LET'S GO DAWN.
Jeff: DAWN HEADING OUT NOW
FOR SAVAII.
DAWN IS NOW CAUGHT UP FOR
SAVAII.
YOU GOT IT, DOWN!
Jeff: DAWN HAS HER BAG.
ALBERT HAS HIS BAG.
DAWN IS FLYING ON THAT WATER.
BRING IT IN!
Jeff: DAWN IS NOW BACK IN
THE LEAD.
OZZY'S GOING TO GO AGAIN FOR
SAVAII.
ALBERT'S GOT TO GET BACK.
UPOLU LOST THEIR LEAD.
YOU GOT IT, MIKAYLA.
Jeff: MIKAYLA NOW OUT FOR
UPOLU.
OZZY HAS THE THIRD BAG.
OZZY IN THE WATER.
BRING IT IN!
GO, MIKAYLA!
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: MIKAYLA AT THE
PLATFORM.
SHE HAS HER THIRD BAG.
OZZY'S BACK WITH THE THIRD BAG
FOR SAVAII PERFORM DAWN BACK OUT
ON THE COURSE.
UPOLU DOES NOT HAVE THE MOMENTUM
GOING.
MIKAYLA FINALLY BACK.
COME ON!
LET'S GO!
Jeff: BRANDON BACK OUT ON
THE COURSE.
BRANDON COULD CATCH HER.
WE ARE TIED 3-3.
GO, BRANDON!
Jeff: DAWN FALLS INTO THE
WATER BEFORE SHE'S EVEN AT THE
PLATFORM.
BRANDON HAS HIS FOURTH BAG.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
GO, GO!
Jeff: BRANDON TAKES THE
LEAD.
DAWN HAS HER FOURTH BAG.
HANG ON, DAWN!
Jeff: BRANDON IS BACK WITH
HIS FOURTH BAG.
DAWN IS BACK WITH HER FOURTH
BAG.
ALBERT HEADING OUT FOR THE FIFTH
AND FINAL BAG FOR UPOLU.
OZZY HEADING OUT FOR THE FIFTH
AND FINAL BAG FOR SAVAII.
IT IS A SHOWDOWN.
YOU GOT IT, OZ!
Jeff: OZZY AND ALBERT.
WHO WILL GET BACK FIRST?
OZZY AND ALBERT BOTH REACH THE
PLATFORM AT THE SAME TIME.
GO!
Jeff: THEY'RE BOTH IN THE
WATER.
HIT IT!
GIVE IT ALL!
Jeff: OZZY'S LOST HIS
BOARD.
OPENING THE DOOR FOR UPOLU.
GO!
EVERYTHING!
BRING HIM IN!
Jeff: BOTH GUYS BACK WITH
THEIR FIFTH AND FINAL BAG.
NOW IT TURNS TO THE TWO OTHER
REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS.
COACH AND EDNA AND ALLYCE AND
WHITNEY NOW IN CHARGE OF THE
GRAPPLING HOOKS.
COACH VERY CLOSE.
HE'S GOT THE FIRST ONE FOR
UPOLU.
NICE AND GENTLE.
Jeff: WHITNEY HAS THE FIRST
BAG FOR SAVAII.
YOU HAVE TO GET ALL FIVE BEFORE
YOU CAN START WORKING ON THIS
PUZZLE.
COME ON, COACH!
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
Jeff: HE'S ALL AROUND IT.
CAN HE HOOK IT?
COACH HAS THE BAG!
LET'S GO, COACH!
Jeff: WHITNEY HAS THE
SECOND BAG FOR SAVAII.
GO, GIRL!
Jeff: COACH, CLOSE.
CAN HE HOOK IT?
COACH HAS HOOKED A THIRD BAG!
FOR UPOLU.
COME ON, SAVAII.
Jeff: WHITNEY VERY CLOSE
ONCE AGAIN.
COACH WITH ANOTHER NICE TOSS.
SWING IT A LITTLE BIT, SWING
IT A LITTLE BIT.
Jeff: COACH HAS HOOKED IT.
WHITNEY HAS HER THIRD BAG FOR
SAVAII.
UPOLU HAS ONE BASKET LEFT.
SAVAII HAS TWO.
YOU GOT IT, WHITT, YOU GOT
IT.
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: WHITNEY HOOKS THE
FOURTH BAG FOR SAVAII.
YOU'RE IN IT!
Jeff: COACH HOOKS THE FIFTH
BAG FOR UPOLU.
COACH HAS BEEN PHENOMENAL WITH
THE GRAPPLING HOOK.
HAVE TO UNTIE ALL FIVE BAGS
BEFORE YOU CAN DROP THE BANNERS.
WHITNEY LOOKING FOR THAT FIFTH
AND FINAL BAG FOR SAVAII.
UPOLU HAS THE LEAD.
COACH NOW UNFURLING THE BANNER.
NICE AND SLOW.
COME OGIRLS!
Jeff: SAVAII STILL WORKING
TO GET BACK IN THIS.
JUST GET THEM DOWN, COACH.
ANY ORDER.
EASY, EASY, EASY DOES IT.
YOU GOT IT!
Jeff: ALLYCE HAS THE FINAL
BAG FOR SAVAII.
SHE'S GOING TO HAVE TO HURRY.
FAR RIGHT, SWITCH.
TAKE FIVE.
GO UNDER ME.
Jeff: EDNA AND COACH
WORKING WITH MIKAYLA AND SOPHIE
TRYING TO FIGURE THIS PUZZLE
OUT.
SAVAII, YOU NEED TO GET ON IT
UPOLU HAVING TO REARRANGE THEIR
PIECES.
UNDER ME.
Jeff: UPOLU VERY CLOSE.
UPOLU WINS IMMUNITY!
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT, BABY!
Jeff: UPOLU,
CONGRATULATIONS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT,
UPOLU.
IN ADDITION, NICE REWARD THAT
I'M SURE YOU'LL USE THIS
AFTERNOON AND WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP, ANOTHER HIDDEN
CLUE THAT WILL HELP YOU FIND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ALL RIGHT, SAVAII, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE THIRD PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME AND SUPPORT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I'M SURE IT WILL MAKE FOR AN
INTERESTING AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
PAPA BEAR IS THE WEAKEST
PERSON ON THE TEAM.
IT'S NOT EVEN THAT HE'S A ZERO.
HE-- HE-- HE SLOWS US DOWN.
HE SHOULD HAVE BEEN THE FIRST
ONE OUT.
I STILL THINK WE'RE THE
STRONGER TRIBE.
WE DID A GOOD JOB.
EVERYBODY DID A GOOD JOB.
WE JUST-- YOU WIN SOME, YOU LOSE
SOMEONE.
IT'S THE WAY IT GOES.
WE LOST THE CHALLENGE TODAY,
AND IT DOES SUCK.
IT'S REALLY BAD FOR MORALE.
WE'RE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
AND WE'VE GOT TO VOTE SOMEBODY
OFF, AND THAT MEANS CUTTING
PEOPLE THAT AREN'T REALLY THAT
GOOD AT CHALLENGES.
DAWN DID A GREAT JOB TODAY, MAN.
SHE KICKED ASS.
IT'S BASICALLY BETWEEN PAPA BEAR
AND COCHRAN.
ARE YOU NERVOUS ABOUT
TONIGHT?
DO YOU HAVE BUTTERFLIES IN YOUR
STOMACH?
I THINK I HAVE GAS.
HOW MUCH EASIER WOULD IT BE TO
BE IN THE GROUP, RIGHT?
ALL THEY'RE SITTING PRETTY.
'CAUSE THOSE FIVE HAVE
CONNECTED.
WE WE GOT PUT ON BARBIE DOLL'S
AND KEN'S TEAM, WE REALLY DID.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW YOU AND I
BECAME--
BECAUSE WE LOOK DIFFERENT.
WE TALK DIFFERENT.
WE SAY DIFFERENT THINGS.
I MEAN, IT'S OBVIOUS, IF I GO
TONIGHT, YOU'RE GOING TOMORROW.
YEAH.
IF YOU GO TONIGHT, I'M GOING
TOMORROW.
RIGHT.
I'M JUST HOPING IT'S NOT ME
TONIGHT.
OBVIOUSLY, I'M HOPING IT'S
NOT ME TONIGHT.
WE ARE UP THE CREEK, BRO.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU GUYS ARE THINKING ALL PAPA
RIGHT.
PAPA BEAR.
IT'S SAD TO SEE, BUT--
I'D RATHER JUST, LIKE, DECIDE
THIS RIGHT NOW AND NOT--
I SAY PAPA.
I'M WITH YOU.
I'M IN.
TELL HIM COCHRAN.
WE HAVE TO.
WE'LL KEEP THE LINE OF
COMMUNICATION OPEN.
IF YOU HEAR ANYTHING--
JUST SO YOU KNOW, IT'S PAPA
BEAR.
SO THIS IS HAPPENING AGAIN?
YEAH.
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
OZZY APPROACHED ME AND SAID
WE'RE GOING TO TELL PAPA BEAR
THAT IT'S YOU, BUT IT'S REALLY
GONNA BE PAPA BEAR.
THE FACT THAT MY NAME KEEPS
COMING UP IS VERY UPSETTING.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
I KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE KIND OF
VIEW IT AS A CHANCE TO GET BACK
IN THE GAME.
I VIEW IT AS A CHANCE FOR,UN,
EXTENDED FAILURE AND JUST MORE
DEPRESSION.
SO I MIGHT DO SOME LAST-MINUTE
SCRAMBLING.
THE PROBLEM IS I ALREADY HAVE
THIS REPUTATION AS THE NERVOUS,
NEUROTIC SCRAMBLER.
IF I RESURRECT THAT BEFORE THE
NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL, I THINK
IT'S GOING TO HURT ME.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GO HOME.
COCHRAN'S GOING HOME.
WHY WOULD THEY CHOOSE HIM?
BECAUSE HE WAS GONNA BE THE
FIRST PERSON OUT.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THAT?
WHAT?
COCHRAN?
WHY?
IT'S OBVIOUS.
HE WAS THE FIRST ONE.
HE GOT SAVED.
THEY SAY IT'S COCHRAN
TONIGHT.
I'M NOT AN IDIOT.
PAPA BEAR IS ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK BIG TIME.
YOU KNOW THEY SAY, "YOU'RE OKAY,
YOU'RE OKAY."
OBVIOUSLY, TO STOP ME FROM
ASKING.
IT'S JOHN COCHRAN TONIGHT.
SURE, I BELIEVE THAT.
I'M AN ASS.
I'M LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
IT'S MY ONLY HOPE AT THIS POINT.
I'M ON MY WAY TO THE SHELTER,
AND PAPA BEAR GOES IN A DEAD
SPRINT FROM THE WATER TO THE
WOODS.
AND PAPA BEAR DISTRIBUTE SPRINT
EVER.
SO I'M LIKE, DID ANYBODY ELSE
SEE THAT?
DYOU SEE PAPA BEAR JUST TALK OFF
RUNNING INTO THE WOODS?
RUNNING?
YEAH, DEAD SPRINT FROM THE
BEACH.
ANYBODY CARE TO JOIN ME?
HE'S UP TO SOMETHING.
JIM AND I WALKED INTO THE WOODS,
AND JUST KIND OF PEAKED AROUND.
AND HE'S JUST LIKE DIGGING
THROUGH THE DIRT LIKE A LITTLE
GOPHER, AND HE'S STILL AT IT.
WOULDN'T IT BE WILD IF HE FOUND
THAT CLUE.
OR THE IDOL.
I'M IN AN EMERGENCY
SITUATION.
I SEARCHED FOR THE IDOL
EVERYWHERE, I COULDN'T FIND IT.
THE BEST THING I CAN DO IS MAKE
THEM THINK I HAVE THE IDOL AND
PLAY THEM AND HOPEFULLY THEY
VOTE FOR JOHN BUT I'M GOING TO
PLAY IT LIKE I FOUND IT, AND I'M
NOT GOING TO SHOW THEM.
I'M JUST GOING TO MAKE IT LIKE A
FOUND IT.
AND HOPEFULLY, THIS WORKS.
DO YOU THINK HE FOUND IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE WAS SEARCHING FOR STUFF.
I MEAN, YOU AND I SAW HIM LIKE
HE WAS SEARCHING.
HE WAS DIGGING.
BUT IT WAS IN DIFFERENT
PLACES.
APPARENTLY JIM AND ALLYCE HAD
SEEN PAPA BEAR FRANTICALLY
DIGGING FOR SOMETHING NEAR A
TREE.
ABOUT FIVE MINUTES LATER, PAPA
BEAR COMES WALTZING INTO CAME
WITH THIS BIG SMILE ON HIS FACE
AND AN EXTRA-LARGE BULGE IN HIS
UNDERPANTS AND HE CLEARLY WANTS
US TO THINK HE HAS THE IDOL.
PAPA BEAR CAME TO ME AND SAID
HE HAD THE IDOL.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, THAT'S THE
VARIABLE IN THERE.
LET'S SAY HE DOES HAVE THE IDOL?
LET'S PROTECT AGAINST THAT.
THE PLAN MIGHT HAVE TO CHANGE.
COCHRAN COULD GO HOME TONIGHT.
IT'S POSSIBLE IT'S AN ACT TO
MAKE YOU THINK HE HAS IT.
I HOPE MY TRIBEMATES SEE THROUGH
THE CHARADE, BUT MY FEAR IS EVEN
IF THEY DON'T BELIEVE HIM, IT'S
NO SKIN OFF THEIR BACK TO SWITCH
THEIR VOTE TO ME FROM PAPA BEAR
AND I'D BE SCREWED.
IT'S INCREDIBLY FUNNY TO
WATCH EVERYBODY SCRAMBLING
AROUND STRESSED OUT THAT PAPA
BEAR MIGHT HAVE THE IDOL.
I MEAN, I ALREADY HAVE IT.
I CAN'T LET ANYONE ELSE KNOW
I HAVE THE IDOL.
I'M JUST HOPING THAT NOTHING
GOES WRONG.
Jeff: SO, COCHRAN, WHEN YOU
WENT BACK TO CAMP AFTER THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU HAD TO BE A
LITTLE CONCERNED BECAUSE YOU
TOOK A LOT OF HEAT FOR NOT
CONTRIBUTING.
I'M TRYING TO MAKE MYSELF
MORE OF AN ASSET TO THE TRIBE,
BOTH ON CAMP AND IN CHALLENGE.
I THINK I PROVED TODAY THAT I AM
CAPABLE IN CHALLENGES.
I MEAN, I'M THE SMALLEST GUY ON
THE TRIBE BUT I WAS REELING IN
WITH THE BEST OF THEM SO I DON'T
SEE HOW MY SIZE WAS ANY OBSTACLE
OR IMPEDIMENT TO MY SUCCESS AT
TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
Jeff: COCHRAN, ARE YOU A
LITTLE DEFENSIVE IN LIFE?
I DON'T NECESSARILY FEEL
THAT'S THE CASE
( LAUGHTER ).
Jeff: PAPA BEAR, WHAT'S
COCHRAN'S BIGGEST PROBLEM IN
THIS GAME?
I THINK, MY OPINION -- THIS
IS MY OPINION ONLY-- THAT
PHYSICALLY, HE'S GOING TO BE A
THREAT TO HIMSELF.
Jeff: COCHRAN, WHERE'S THE
LEADERSHIP AT ON THIS TRIBE?
THERE ARE MULTIPLE LAYERS OF
LEADERSHIP ON THE TRIBE.
THE MOST OBVIOUS IS TO SAY OZZY
IS OUR LEADER.
WE FOLLOW HIS LEAD IN TERMS OF
LEARNING HOW TO SURVIVE THESE
ELEMENTS.
Jeff: PAPA BEAR, OZZY THE
LEADER?
EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE THE
LEADER AND THIS IS A GAME WITH
A-TYPE PERSONALITIES.
NONE OF THESE PEOPLE HERE SIT ON
THE COUCH ALL DAY.
Jeff: PAPA BEAR, WHAT'S
YOUR BACKGROUND PROFESSIONALLY?
I'M A RETIRED NEW YORK CITY
POLICE DETECTIVE.
Jeff: SO YOU ARE, CLEARLY,
A LEADER?
I LIKE TO BE A LEADER, BUT
FOR SOME REASON, IN THIS TEAM,
I'M NOT A LEADER.
FOR SOME REASON, THE FIVE HAS
JUST TAKEN CONTROL.
AND I REALLY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
IN COMMON WITH ANY OF THEM.
Jeff: DAWN, ARE YOU
NOTICING PEOPLE START TO GROUP
BASED ON SIMILAR LIKES OR AGE OR
BACKGROUNDS?
YEAR, I MEAN, I THINK ANY
GROUP IS BASED ON SIMILARITY,
KIND OF COMMUNITY.
I THINK SOMETIMES PAPA BEAR,
MYSELF, AND COCHRAN, MIGHT NOT
HAVE THINGS IN COMMON.
BUT I SEE IT SHIFTING THROUGHOUT
THE DAY.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I SEE IT AS
LOCKED.
DAWN.
HE SAID YOU, ME, AND COCHRAN.
THE TRUTH SWE'RE NOT IN THE
FIVE.
WE'RE NOT IN THEIR GROUP, ANDUN
THAT.
SO IT'S OKAY TO SAY IT BECAUSE
IT'S REAL.
Jeff: KIM, YOU'RE NOT
BUYING THIS.
NO, ACTUALLY, I THINK DAWN
WAS RIGHT OAND I THINK PAPA BEAR
FEELS HE'S ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK
TONIGHT SO I REALLY THINK A LOT
OF HIS COMMENT ARE REALLY
INTENDED TO STIR THINGS UP.
I DON'T HAVE TO STIR.
IF I'M IN THE THREE, I DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY.
IF I GET VOTE OUT, I'M ONLY
THREE.
THERE'S NOT A THREE.
YOU NEED TO WORRY ABOUT IT
BECAUSE YOU'RE IN THE FIVE.
Jeff: JIM, GIVEN MY THOUGHT
ABOUT THE IDOL?
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
I MEAN, I SEE IT AS A VERY VERY,
VERY SIGNIFICANT TOOL AN IDOL
PLAYED THIS EARLY ON, FOR
EXAMPLE, REALLY GIVES YOU THREE
MORE DAYS.
THAT IS IS WHAT "SURVIVOR" IS
ALL ABOUT.
YOU SURVIVE ONE DAY AT A TIME.
Jeff: OZZY WERE YOU VOTED
OUT HOLDING ON TO AN IDOL.
YES.
Jeff: SO WHAT JIM SAYS IT
GETS YOU THREE MORE DAYS IS NOT
NECESSARILY TRUE.
YES, THIS IS POSSIBLY THAT
COULD BE SOMETHING THAT COULD
CHANGE THE GAME TOTALLY AND
COMPLETELY.
I KNOW WHENEVER SOMEONE TAKES A
WALK YOU'RE DEFINITELY KEEPING
YOUR EYES PEELED.
Jeff: COCHRAN, YOU'RE A
BRIGHT GUY.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN FIND THE
IDOL?
UHM.
IT'S POSSIBLE.
I JUST THINK THAT YOU HAVE TO
WEIGH THE PROS AND CONS OF
SEARCHING FOR THE IDOL.
IT MAKES YOU LOOK VERY, VERY
SUSPICIOUS AND IT MAKES YOU LOOK
LIKE YOU DON'T TRUST YOUR TRIBE.
IT'S A FOSTER OF TRUST ON THE
TRIBE AND SEARCHING FOR AN
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IDOL IS NOT
NECESSARILY THE BEST WAY TO
AVOID THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
ALLYCE, YOU'RE UP.
PAPA BEAR, JUST IN CASE YOU HAVE
THAT IDOL.
Y.
I THINK YOU'RE A SWEETHEART,
A REALLY GREAT GUYS, BUT YOU
MAKE ME ANXIOUS AND I DON'T NEED
ANY MORE ANXIETY IN MY LIFE.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, PAPA BEAR.
COCHRAN.
ONE VOTE COCHRAN.
JIM.
ONE VOTE PAPA BEAR, ONE VOTE
COCHRAN, ONE VOTE JIM.
PAPA BEAR.
THAT'S TWO VOTES PAPA BEAR.
THAT'S THREE VOTES PAPA BEAR.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC," PAPA
BEAR.
THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
PAPA BEAR, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
GOOD-BYE, EVERYBODY.
Jeff: WELL, THE GOOD NEWS
IS, BOTH OF YOUR VOTES AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL HAVE BEEN DECISIVE.
THE BAD NEWS IS YOU'RE DOWN ONE
MEMBER AND THE LOOMING QUESTION
IS ARE YOU VOTING OUT THE RIGHT
PEOPLE?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
AT SAVAII, THE NEW MASTERMIND
IS COCHRAN.
THIS IS THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY TO DEVASTATE OZZY.
IT'S A SURVIVOR MOVIE.
I KNOW.
Jeff: AND BRANDON'S
PARANOIA HITS NEW HEIGHTS.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM ON OUR
HANDS.
ALBERT, MIKAYLA AND SOPHIE HAVE
SOMETHING GOING ON.
BRENDAN IS A SMALL RUSSELL
HANTZ.
NO VOTES WHEN THEY'RE AGAINST
ARE YOU FAIR.
I DON'T THINK I DESERVED TO GO
HOME TODAY.
I THINK COCHRAN DESERVED TO BE
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
MY STRATEGY RIGHT NOW IS TO DO
EVERY DUEL I CAN SUCCESSFULLY,
AND FIGET BACK INTO THE GAME I'M
GOING TO GO TO THE BLUE TEAM
BECAUSE I'M NOT GOING BACK TO
THE SAME TEAM THAT JUST VOTED ME
OUT.