Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": SINCE THE MERGE, KIM
HAS BROUGHT THE WOMEN TOGETHER
TO TAKE CONTROL OF THE GAME,
SENDING THREE MEN IN A ROW TO
THE JURY.
TROYZAN WAS NEXT IN LINE, BUT
PLAYED A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL TO
SAVE HIMSELF.
I'M NOT GOING TO JOIN THAT
GROUP.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
UNABLE TO FIND A SECOND IDOL, HE
DECIDED TO FAKE ONE.
I START ACTING LIKE I'M
ZIPPING SOMETHING UP, LETTING
THEM THINK I HAVE AN IDOL.
Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE-- TROYZAN WINS
IMMUNITY.
YES!
Jeff: TROYZAN WON.
YES, YES, YES!
Jeff: AND WAS SAFE FROM THE
VOTE.
DON'T ( BLEEP ) WITH ME.
Jeff: TROYZAN TRIED TO FLIP
THE GAME IN HIS FAVOR.
WHAT'S TO STORT YOU AND
TARZAN AND CHRISTINA GETTING RID
OF A STRONG PERSON?
TROY IS ON TO SOMETHING.
IT'S SOMETHING I HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
TROYZAN CONTINUED TO TRY TO
CHANGE THE VOTE.
KIM, CHELSEA, SABRINA AND KAT.
THOSE FOUR CAN DO WHATEVER THEY
WANT.
I TOLD THESE GUYS YOU CAN GO
FROM GETTING VOTED OUT TONIGHT,
TARZAN, GETTING VOTED OUT
TONIGHT, LEIF, GETTING VOTED OUT
TONIGHT TO GUARANTEE YOURSELF
BEING AT FIVE IF THEY WOULD VOTE
KIM OUT.
Jeff: IN THE END, THE WOMEN
STUCK WITH KIM AND CONTINUED
THEIR DOMINANCE OVER THE MEN.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT, THE
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, LEIF.
SENDING LEIF TO THE JURY.
TARZAN AND TROYZAN, IT WOULD
APPEAR YOU HAVE TWO OPTIONS--
WIN IMMUNITY OR FIND A WAY IN.
EIGHT ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE
VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
WE'RE DOWN TO EIGHT, AND LOOK
WHERE WE ARE NOW, TWO BOYS LEFT.
SO NOW WE'RE IN A HOPELESS
SITUATION UNLESS THE BOYS WIN
IMMUNITIES.
SO IF I WAS TRYING TO PLAY THE
ODDS IN MY FAVOR, THE SMARTEST
THING I COULD DO IS GO WITH WHAT
THE GIRLS WANT ME TO DO, RATHER
THAN RISK BEING EXPOSED AS A
PERSON ON TROYZAN'S SIDE.
YOU OKAY?
I THINK HE'S JUST DOING
EVERYTHING HE CAN, YOU KNOW?
TRIBAL WAS REALLY INTERESTING
TONIGHT.
TROY THREW MY NAME OUT,
DEFINITELY THROWS ME A CURVEBALL
IN THIS GAME, LIKE, I WAS NOT
PLANNING ON BEING A TARGET SO
EARLY ON.
I GET NERVOUS, THAT'S FOR SURE.
WHICH IS FINE 'CAUSE I TRUST
YOU GUYS.
I KIND OF FEEL LIKE TONIGHT
SEALED THE DEAL A LITTLE BIT
WITH THE WOMEN'S ALLIANCE.
I THINK THAT EVERYBODY FEELS
KIND OF MARRIED TO OUR ALLIANCE,
LOCKED IN, SO I'M JUST TRYING TO
STAY CALM AND KEEP EVERYBODY
HAPPY AND HOPEFULLY GET RID OF
TROY BY THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
RIGHT NOW, I'M ON MY OWN.
I MEAN, THERE'S TARZAN, BUT HE'S
NOT WITH ME.
SO I STILL FEEL LIKE I'M, YOU
KNOW, ONE MAN AGAINST ALL THE
WOMEN.
AND TARZAN.
THEY THINK I HAVE AN IDOL THAT I
HAVEN'T PLAYED, SO THAT WILL BE
TO MY ADVANTAGE.
BUT RIGHT NOW, I NEED TO WIN
EVERY SINGLE IMMUNITY, ONE MAN
VERSUS ALL THE WOMEN.
BRING IT ON.
ALL RIGHT.
TREE MAIL!
YEAH.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT COULD BE A
REWARD.
ALL RIGHT.
"IT'S NOT PHYSICAL EXERTION,
EARNING REWARD TODAY.
YOUR POWERS OF PERCEPTION WILL
HELP YOU GET AWAY."
ARE WE GONNA HAVE TO CHOOSE
PEOPLE?
I'M HOPING WHOEVER WINS GET
TO TAKE ANOTHER PERSON ON A
REWARD, AND I THINK IT'S JUST
TIME FOR ME TO BE ABLE TO GO ON
SOMETHING.
YOU'RE PICKING ME, RIGHT?
YEAH.
I THINK I HAVE A GREAT
RELATIONSHIP WITH KIM, SO IF I
WIN I CAN PICK KIM, AND IF SHE
WINS SHE CAN PICK ME.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
I HAVE CRAZIER HAIR THAN
THAT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S REWARD
CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
YOU'RE GOING TO ANSWER A SERIES
OF QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR
TRIBEMATES.
I'LL THEN TALLY THE RESULTS.
FOR THE CHALLENGE, YOUR JOB IS
TO TRY TO GUESS WHAT THE GROUP
SAID AS A WHOLE TO EACH
QUESTION.
THAT MAY DIFFER FROM WHAT YOU
SAID INDIVIDUALLY.
EACH TIME YOU GET ONE RIGHT, YOU
GET TO CHOP ANOTHER TRIBE
MEMBER'S ROPE.
AFTER THREE CHOPS, YOUR VERY
LIFE-LIKE "SURVIVOR" DOLL WILL
FALL INTO THE FIRE AND YOUR
CHANCES IN THIS CHALLENGE WILL
GO UP IN SMOKE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
YES.
Jeff: THE WINNER WILL BE
TAKEN HAVE A HELICOPTER TO A
BEAUTIFUL ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL
ENJOY A PICNIC.
OH!
WOW!
Jeff: EVERYTHING YOU NEED
TO HAVE A NICE AFTERNOON AND GET
SOME FOOD IN YOUR BELLY.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
YES N.
YES!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
OKAY, I HAVE TALLIED THE RESULTS
REMEMBER, YOU'RE LOOKING FOR THE
CONSENSUS.
FIRST QUESTION, "HODOES NOT
DESERVE TO STILL BE HERE?"
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
WOW, WE'RE ALL ACROSS THE BOARD.
CORRECT ANSWER, THE GROUP SAITD
PERSON WHO DOES NOT DESERVE TO
STILL BE HERE IS CHRISTINA.
KIM GOT IT RIGHT.
CHELSEA GOT IT RIGHT.
TROYZAN GOT IT RIGHT.
CHRISTINA, THAT IS A BIG SLAP IN
THE FACE, ISN'T IT?
IT IS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
Jeff: TROYZAN IS FIRST UP.
KAT GETS THE FIRST HIT.
NO WORDS AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, TROY, YOU KNOW.
ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: CHELSEA HITS TARZAN.
NEXT QUESTION, "WHO WOULD YOU
TRUST WITH YOUR LIFE?
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
CORRECT ANSWER IS KIM.
OH, KIMBO.
Jeff: CHRISTINA GOT IT
RIGHT, CHELSEA GOT IT RIGHT,
ALICIA GOT IT RIGHT.
CHELSEA.
Jeff: CHELSEA, TOOK HER
FIRST HIT FROM CHRISTINA.
CHELSEA GIVES HER SECOND HIT TO
TROYZAN, AND WITH THAT, TROYZAN
FIRST ONE OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
AAAH, MY ASS.
THIS IS MY ISLAND!
AND NOW HE'S PART OF THE
ISLAND.
IT'S ASHES.
AND HE'S BECOME THE MOLECULAR
SUBSTRATE OF THIS ISLAND SO HE
DOES BELONG ON THIS ISLAND.
Jeff: EVIDENCE JUST GETTING
READY TO SAY THAT.
NEXT QUESTION, "WHO MOST NEEDS
A WAKE-UP CALL IN LIFE?"
I HATE THAT QUESTION.
Jeff: EVERYBODY REVEAL.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: EVERYBODY SAD KAT
EXCEPT KAT.
KAT SAID CHRISTINA.
COME ON, MAN.
Jeff: CORRECT ANSWER, KAT.
MOST NEEDS A WAKE-UP CALL.
OH, NO.
Jeff: TARZAN TAKES HIS
SECOND HIT.
ONE HIT AWAY FROM BEING OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
CHELSEA TAKES HER SECOND HIT.
CHELSEA IS NOW ONE HIT AWAY FROM
BEING OUT.
LOVE YOU.
OH!
I'M FEELING THE LOVE.
I'M FEELING IT.
Jeff: TARZAN IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
IT'S NOTHING PERSON.
NO!
Jeff: SABRINA TAKES HER
FIRST HIT.
CHRISTINA TAKES HER FIRST HIT
CHELSEA IS OUT OF THE GAME.
NEXT QUESTION, "WHO IS THE
BIGGEST POSER?"
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
( LAUGHS ).
Jeff: EVERYBODY REVEAL.
WOW!
Jeff: EVERYBODY SAYS
TROYZAN EXCEPT ALICIA WHO SAID
CHRISTINA.
WHAT?
Jeff: CHRISTINA YOU GET AN
ANSWER EVERY TIME.
HOW AM I A POSER?
Jeff: CORRECT ANSWER IS
TROYZAN.
KAT GOT IT RIGHT, KIM GOT IT
RIGHT, SABRINA GOT IT RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD, KIM!
Jeff: SABRINA TAKES HER
SECOND HIT.
KIM TAKES HER FIRST HIT.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOCK OUT ONE!
Jeff: ALICIA TAKES HER
SECOND HIT.
NEXT QUESTION, "WHO DOES THE
LEAST FOR THEIR TRIBE?
THIS IS HARD.
Jeff: EVERYBODY REVEAL.
CORRECT ANSWER IS SABRINA.
KIM GOT IT RIGHT, CHRISTINA GOT
IT RIGHT, ALICIA GOT IT RIGHT.
OH, HAVE MERCY!
SORRY, KAT.
WHAT?
WHAT DID I DO TO YOU?
Jeff: KAT IS DOWN TO HER
LAST.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
YOU GUYS ARE CRAZY.
WHATEVER?
Jeff: ALICIA KNOCKS KAT OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
KIM HEADS TO SABRINA, AND
SABRINA IS UP ON THE OF THE
CHALLENGE.
OH!
WHAT GETS ME IS I CAN SEE THE
LITTLE SKELETON THAT JUST HANGS
ON THERE.
Jeff: NEXT QUESTION, "WHO
WOULD YOU MOST LIKE TO BE
STRANDED WITH ON AN ISLAND?"
KIM SAYS HERSELF.
CHRISTINA SAYS TROYZAN.
UNFORTUNATELY, CHRISTINA, THE
CORRECT ANSWER WAS KIM.
QIM GOT HERSELF RIGHT, AND
ALICIA GOT IT RIGHT.
OUT OF NOWHERE, STARTING TO DUMP
RAIN.
ALICIA DIDN'T EVEN HESITATE.
AND WITH THAT, CHRISTINA'S SHOT
AT WINNING THIS CHALLENGE GOES
UP IN FLAMES.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
NEXT QUESTION, "WHO DO YOU HOPE
TO NEVER SEE AGAIN AFTER THE
GAME?"
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: REVEAL.
BOTH KIM AND ALICIA SAY TROYIAN
SWRAN.
KIM YOU HAVE TWO CHOPS LEFT,
ALICIA YOU HAVE ONE, THAT MEANS
IF YOU'RE BOTH RIGHT, KIM WINS
THIS CHALLENGE.
CORRECT ANSWER, TROYZAN.
KIM, TAKE YOUR LAST SHOT.
ALICIA'S OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
KIM WINS REWARD.
YA, KIM!
Jeff: KIM, NICE JOB.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO BE
PICKED UP IN A HELICOPTER, TAKEN
TO A NICE, BEAUTIFUL BEACH,
WHERE YOU'LL HAVE A PICNIC
LUNCH.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON.
TO GO WITH YOU.
OH, WOW.
ALICIA.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: KIM IF HUONE MORE
CHOICE WOULD IT BE AN EASY ONE?
NO IT WOULD BE REALLY, REALLY
HARD.
LET'S MAKE IT DIFFICULT
BECAUSE YOU HAVE ONE MORE
CHOICE.
I'M SORRY.
CHELSEA.
REALLY?
WOW!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
OH, MY GOD.
I'M GOING TO CRY.
THANK YOU.
I'M SORRY.
THIS GIRL NEVER EATS, KAT, AND
YOU KNOW IT.
I THINK IT'S PRETTY
REVEALING.
Jeff: WHO SHE CHOSE?
IT SHOWS EXACTLY WHERE
EVERYONE STANDS, EXACTLY.
KIM AND CHELSEA AND ALICIA ARE
THE TOP DOGS.
THESE GUYS ARE AT THE BOTTOM.
SORRY.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT TO SAVE
MYSELF.
THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT WAS.
HMM.
Jeff: YOU GUYS GRAB YOUR
STUFF.
THE BIRD IS WAITING FOR YOU.
I'M SORRY.
WHATEVER.
I PLANTED A FEW SEEDS.
SO THEY START TO THINK LIKE,
MAYBE I REALLY AM ON THE BOTTOM.
AND NOW I'M GOING TO REALLY TOY
WITH THEIR MINDS.
WHOOO!
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S LIKE A RIDE.
DUDE, THIS IS AWESOME.
GLAD Y'ALL ARE HERE WITH ME,
NO ONE ELSE I WANTED TO BRING.
I'VE NEVER BEEN ON A
HELICOPTER SO HELICOPTER RIDE
DEFINITELY ONE OF THE TOP 10
THINGS I'VE EVER DONE.
IT WAS VERY, VERY COOL.
WE SAW BEAUTIFUL WATERFALLS.
THIS IS SO CRAZY.
IT WAS LIKE A ROLLER COASTER
RIDE.
WE WERE LOVING THE WHOLE LIKE
SWOOP THING, SWOOP DOWN BY THE
WAVES.
OH, MY GOD!
AND THEN OF COURSE TO COME
HERE WITH TWO OF MY FRIENDS CAN
THE GAME, I DON'T KNOW IF IT
HATES ANY BETTER.
THE REWARD WAS AWESOME, BUT I
CAN'T DECIDE IF I'M ENJOYING IT
OR NOT.
THE HARD PART, I FEEL LIKE A LOT
OF PEOPLE PROBABLY WENT HOME
FEELING REALLY CRUDDY.
YOU COULDN'T TAKE EVERYONE,
LIKE-- THE ONE WHO GOT A BEATING
WAS CHRISTINA.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO DO
SOME DAMAGE CONTROL WITH OUR
ALLIANCE WHEN WE GET BACK.
( LAUGHS )
THE FOOD WAS INCREDIBLE AND I'M
TRYING TO CAMP OUT BUT IT'S
REALLY HARD.
MOSTLY I'M SCARED RIGHT NOW NOU
WITH WHAT HAPPENED WITH THE
REWARD CHALLENGE.
THIS LITERALLY COULD BE THE DAY
THE TIDE TURNS FOR ME.
YOU KNOW TROY IS BACK AT CAMP
GOING, EVERYBODY LOVES KIM."
IT'S A DISASTER.
SO, I TOOK IT REALLY PERSONAL
BECAUSE I'M HUNGRY, TOO, AND I
HATE WHEN KIM MADE THAT COMMENT,
"SHE'S HUNGRY."
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN
SHE'S HUNGRY?
WE'RE ALL HUNGRY.
AND TROY WITH HIS COMMENT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU'RE NOT GRASPING IT.
THAT'S NOT THE TRUTH.
YOU THINK IT'S ABOUT FOOD.
KAT, KAT, THIS ISN'T ABOUT FOOD
TODAY.
IT'S STRATEGY.
BECAUSE OF THE REWARD AND THE
FACT THAT KIM WENT OFF WITH
CHELSEA AND ALICIA, IT GAVE ME
THE OPPORTUNITY TO SPEAK TO FIVE
PEOPLE I NORMALLY WOULDN'T HAVE
A CHANCE TO SIT DOWN AND POWWOW
WITH.
RIGHT NOW, WHY AREN'T YOU THERE
RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW, AND I'LL DEAL
WITH IT WHEN SHE GETS BACK.
AND WHEN YOU CAN PUT FEAR IN
THESE PEOPLE'S HEAD YOU'RE ONE
STEP AHEAD.
HEY, PEOPLE, I'LL PLAY WITH YOUR
MINDS ALL THE TIME.
KAT, YOU GOTTA GRASP, LIKE,
WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOU THINK YOU'RE IN THE KNOW,
WHEN YOU'RE ACTUALLY NOT.
AND I'M NOT SAYING THIS, YOU
KNOW, BECAUSE I'M SOME GUY ON
THE OUTS.
YOU NEED TO WAKE UP.
NO, YOU NEED TO RELAX.
NO, YOU NEED TO WAKE UP.
WAKE UP AND SMELL THE COFFEE
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE ALL PISSED OFF-- GET MAD.
YOU SHOULD GET MAD.
BECAUSE THOSE GIRLS ARE TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF YOU AND YOU'RE
STARTING TO REALIZE IT AND
YOU'RE GETTING PISSED OFF.
I'M PISSED BECAUSE KIM DIDN'T
TAKE ME, AND I'M PISSED BECAUSE
I HAVE TO LISTEN TO TROYZAN
ABOUT, LIKE, I'M A FOLLOWER AND
I DON'T MAKE ANY DECISIONS FOR
MYSELF AND KIM IS THE LEAD
PLAYER.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
THE TWO PEOPLE SHE FEELS LIKE
ARE NOT GOING TO FOLD SHE KEPT
HERE.
I KNOW, AND I HAVE TO DEAL
WITH IT, AND I DON'T WANT TO.
LISTEN, LISTEN, LISTEN.
TROY WAS MAKING ME SO ANGRY.
I'M SICK AND TIRED OF HIM SAYING
THAT.
IT'S LIKE HE SAYS THEY'RE THE
FINAL THREE.
LIKE, LIKE I-- NOT TRUE.
DON'T LET HIM GET IN YOUR
HEAD.
MY FEAR IS I DON'T WANT TO GO
DOWN AS A WEAK PLAYER, AND I'M
GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO
MAKE SURE THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
AND IF THAT HAPPENS AND IT MEANS
ME HAVING TO VOTE KIM OUT, FINE.
I'M TRYING TO EXTRACT AS MUCH
AS I CAN OUT OF CHRISTINA.
ALL RIGHT.
KAT NEEDS TO BE SOOTHED.
SHE'S A HOT MESS RIGHT NOW.
BUT RIGHT NOW, TROY IS VERY
SAVVY.
IF ANYONE CAN GO THROUGH THIS
DAILY GAMEALL THE WAY AND WIN
EVERY LAST SINGLE CHALLENGE,
IT'S HIM, HANDS DOWN.
WHAT WOULD BE YOUR MASTER PLAN,
TROY?
KIM CAN WIN JUST AS MUCH AS
ME.
OKAY.
EVERYONE LIKES HER.
CHELSEA IS RIGHT NEXT TO HER.
RIGHT NOW, I'M THE SITTING DUCK,
BUT IF YOU GUYS WANT ME TO GIVE
YOU A VOTE, I'LL GIVE YOU A
VOTE.
WE JUST NEED ONE GIRL TO
TURN.
THE TRUTH IS, SABRINA, I
MEAN, IT'S EITHER ME, YOU-- I
MEAN, YOU KNOW, WHATEVER IS
GOING ON, SO WE HAVE TO THINK OF
ANOTHER OPTION.
OH, YEAH.
OBVIOUSLY, I'M NOT ON TROY'S
SIDE, BUT THE MAIN REASON I PUT
IT OUT THERE, I WANTED TO SEE
WHO WAS EASILY SWAYED.
CHRISTINA WITHIN SECONDS OF ME
EVEN PROPOSING IT "I THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA."
SHE SWAYS LIKE THE WIND.
I DON'T TRUST HER AT ALL.
HEY, WOW.
THAT WAS QUICK.
YES, IT WAS.
WANT TO SIT HERE?
OH.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT
RIGHT NOW.
WHEN KIM CAME BACK, THERE'S A
LOT OF THINGS THAT WERE GOING
THROUGH MY MIND THAT I DIDN'T
KNOW IF THOSE REMEMBER SEEDS
THAT TROY PUT THERE, OR IF THOSE
WERE JUST RIDICULOUS IDEAS THAT
WERE MAKING ME FEEL DIFFERENTLY
ABOUT KIM.
KAT, YOU WANT SALAD?
NO.
I WAS JUST-- I WAS DEVASTATED.
AND I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
SAY TO HER.
WILL YOU PLEASE COME TALK TO
ME, PLEASE?
DO NOT BE MAD.
I'M FURIOUS.
I KNOW.
LIKE, THAT--
DO YOU WANT ME TO TALK FIRST
OR DO YOU WANT TO TALK?
GO AHEAD.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY.
THIS IS WHAT I WANTED TO TELL
YOU.
KAT, I ADORE YOU.
YOU'RE ONE OF MY VERY FAVORITE
PEOPLE HERE.
WE'RE PLAYING A GAME FOR $1
MILLION.
I WAS PLANNING TO TAKE YOU THIS
MORNING.
IT WASN'T ABOUT THE REWARD IT
WAS JUST ABOUT BEING PICKED
BECAUSE EVERYBODY HERE THINKS OF
ME AS A FOLLOWER PLAYER LIKE
CHRISTINA BECAUSE OF THAT PICK
TODAY.
WELL, IT'S NOT EASY FOR ME
TODAY, EITHER.
THIS IS MY WORST DAY OUT HERE
AND IT SHOULDN'T BE, AND I'M NOT
THROWING MYSELF A PITY PARTY.
I'M TELLING YOU THIS IS
LITERALLY THE WORST THING THAT
HAPPENED TO ME SINCE THE GAME
STARTED THAT I WON THE FREAKING
CHALLENGE TODAY.
I WISH I DIDN'T WIN IT.
WHY WOULD YOU WISH YOU DIDN'T
WIN THE CHALLENGE?
IT'S NOT A FUN POSITION TO BE
IT IN.
ALL I'M ASKING YOU TO DO RIGHT
NOW IS HAVE A BIGGER PICTURE
PERSPECTIVE.
LIKE I--
YOU KNOW, I THINK MY CHOICE
TO NOT CHOOSE KAT TODAY WAS THE
FIRST DECISION I HAVE MADE THAT
WAS NOT STRATEGIC, AND I THINK
I'M PAYING FOR IT NOW.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
DO WE KILL IT?
NO.
OH, SHOOT!
WE HAVE TO SHOOT THAT THING.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
ALL RIGHT, WE NEED A ROPE.
WE'RE ALL AROUND THE
CAMPFIRE, AND I JUST KIND OF
GLANCE OVER AND THIS GIANT PIG,
I MEAN 160, 170-POUND PIG GOES
WALK RIGHT ACROSS THE PATH.
I'M LIKE IS THIS AN ILLUSION?
AM I SEEING WHAT I'M REALLY
SEEING?
WHAT THE HELL?
TROY!
HE NEED AN AXE, CHRISTINA.
AN AXE.
WE'RE GETTING READY TO COOK
RICE-- OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, WE'RE SITTING DOWN
ENJOYING RICE, AND WE SEE A
FREAKING BIG-ASS PIG COME BACK.
LIKE BACON AND HAM.
YOU ALL WANT SOME PIG?
KILL THE PIG!
YOU CAN REDEEM YOURSELF,
TROY.
KILL THE PIG.
I JOIN IN FOR FUN'S SAKE,
JUST TO GIVE MYSELF A LAUGH.
BUT THEN I START THINKING HOW
FOOLISH DOES THIS LOOK.
LIKE, THESE GIRLS ARE ALL
RUNNING AROUND, CHASING A PIG,
AND NOT KNOWING WHAT THE HELL
THEY'RE GOING TO DO WITH IT ONCE
THEY CATCH IT.
TROY, GET IT FROM BEHIND.
OH!
OH, MY GOD.
( SCREAMING )
NO!
THEY THINK, LIKE, WE'RE GOING
TO KILL IT IN FIVE MINUTE AND
CUT A LEG OFF AND HAVE HAM
SANDWICHES ALL AROUND.
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU THE
INTELLIGENCE OF MY TRIBE
I HAVE NO EXPERIENCE WITH
CATCHING PIGS, BUT THE PIG
COMING INTO CAMP IS AWESOME FOR
ME RIGHT NOW.
IT BREAKS TENSION AND I CAN
ALREADY FEEL, LIKE, WALLS COMING
DOWN.
THE PIG IS CUTE.
I'M SORRY, I'M NOT KILLING THAT
PIG.
WE COULD DEFINITELY KEEP IT AS A
PET.
( LAUGHTER ).
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
YES.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TROYZAN, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
SLIDE DOWN A SLIPPERY COURSE,
GRABBING ROPE RINGS ALONG THE
WAY.
ONCE YOU HAVE YOUR RING, YOU
MUST LAND IT ON A HOOK.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH MOVES ON
TO THE NEXT ROUND.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, ONE IN SEVEN SHOT AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
WE'VE DRAWN FOR SPOTS.
FIRST ROUND.
IT IS CHELSEA TAKING ON ALICIA.
THE WINNER OF THIS ROUND MOVES
ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
GETTING LUBED UP.
THAT OIL IS GOING TO HELP YOU
GET DOWN THIS COURSE QUICKLY.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU'VE GOT TO HIT IT HARDER THAN
THAT.
BOTH ARE GOING TO COME UP SHORT.
ALICIA TRYING TO RUN ON THIS.
CHELSEA SLIP-SLIDING ON IT.
IT'S NOT EASY.
OH, OH, OH!
Jeff: NOW IT'S A RING TOSS.
FIRST ONE TO LAND IT MOVES ON TO
THE NEXT ROUND.
LOOKING TO MOVE ON TO THE NEXT
ROUND AND HAVE A SHOT AT
IMMUNITY.
GOT TO HIT IT HERE OH!
JUST MISSED IT.
CHELSEA TRYING TO STRATEGIZE.
CHELSEA NAILS IT.
CHELSEA MOVING ON TO THE NEXT
ROUND.
NICE JOB.
Jeff: NEXT ROUND WE HAVE
KAT TAKING ON SABRINA.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
SABRINA RIGHT TO THE RING.
SHE IS UP AND HEADING TO THE END
WHILE KAT IS STILL TENTATIVELY
TRYING TO GET TO IT.
SABRINA WITH AN EARLY LEAD.
SHE CAN DO IT WITH ONE SHOT BUT
SHE'S SHORT.
KAT STILL NOTHERE.
NOW KAT TAKES HER FIRST SHOT.
KAT NAILS IT.
KAT MOVES ON.
NEXT ROUND WE HAVE TROYZAN
TAKING ON TARZAN.
BATTLE OF THE 'SWRANS.
WINNER MOVES ON.
LOSER IS OUT.
SURVIVORS READY.
GO TARZAN LAUNCHES HARD.
TROYZAN COMES UP A LITTLE SHORT.
GO, GO, GO.
CRAWL, CRAWL, CRAWL.
Jeff: TROYZAN TAKES HIS
FIRST SHOT, MISSES.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
TAKE YOUR TIME, TARZAN.
YOU GOT IT, BABY.
Jeff: TARZAN JUST MISSES,
OPENING THE DOOR FOR TROYZAN.
DO IT!
Jeff: TROYZAN CAN WIN IT
RIGHT HERE.
HE JUST MISSES.
HURRY, GO.
TARZAN, YOU CAN TOTALLY DO THIS.
TARZAN IT'S YOUR GAME.
TARZAN REALLY TAKING HIS TIME
AND IT PAYS OFF.
TARZAN MOVES ON.
TROYZAN IS OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
NEXT ROUND, WE HAVE CHRISTINA
TAKING ON KIM.
WINNER MOVES ON.
HAVE FUN, GIRLS.
Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
SLIDE!
Jeff: KIM LAUNCHES HARD.
COMES UP SHORT.
CHRISTINA BARELY GETS DOWN THE
COURSE.
KIM NOT MESSING AROUND, MAKING
QUICK WORK ON HER KNEES.
CHRISTINA IS VERY SLOW.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
Jeff: KIM NAILS IT.
KIM MOVING ON TO THE NEXT ROUND!
TROYZAN'S SO PISSED.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SECOND
ROUND.
WE'VE DRAWN FOR SPOTS.
IT IS CHELSEA TAKING ON KAT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
FOR THE SECOND ROUND, THERE ARE
TWO RINGS TO GATHER, AND TWO
RINGS TO HOOK.
THE WINNER MOVES ON TO
THEIFIABLE ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
KAT LAUNCHES HERSELF.
DOWN THE COURSE.
KAT SCRAMBLING FOR THE TWO RINS.
KAT SHUFFLING ALONG THE COURSE.
COME ON!
Jeff: GOT TO STICK BOTH
RINGS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHICH HOOK.
ANY HOOK WILL DO.
CHELSEA WITHHER FIRST SHOT LANDS
HER FIRST
RING.
KAT LANDS HER FIRST RING.
CHELSEA LANDS HER SECOND RING?
GOOD JOB!
Jeff: CHELSEA MOVING ON TO
THE FINALS.
NEXT TWO.
TARZAN NOW HITTING ON KIM.
THE WINNER MOVES ON TO THE FINAL
AGAINST CHELSEA.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
KIM WITH A BIG LAUNCH.
ONCE AGAIN, USING THE KNEE
STRATEGY, AND IT'S WORKING.
KIM FLYING DOWN THE COURSE.
IN WITH A BIG LEAD RIGHT OUT OF
THE GATE.
KIM HOOKS HER FIRST RING.
TAKES TARZAN A WHILE TO GET
HERE.
AND HE APPEARS TO BE IN NO HURRY
EVEN NOW.
KIM NAILS IT.
KIM MOVES ON TO THE FINAL.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S FINE WITH
ME.
Jeff: FOR THE FINAL ROUND,
IT IS CHELSEA TAKING ON KIM.
LET'S GO, LADIES!
Jeff: YOU'VE GOT TO HOOK
THREE WINGS THIS TIME.
WINNER WINS IMMUNITY.
IS SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
CHELSEA VERSUS KIM.
BOTH LAUNCH THEMSELVES DOWN THE
COURSE.
KIM WITH A BIT OF A LEAD.
BUT SHE'S GOT A STRATEGY THAT'S
BEEN PROVEN TO WORK.
KIM'S ON HER KNEES.
CHELSEA SORT OF SHUFFLES.
KIM WITH HER FIRST SHOT, MISSES.
CHELSEA JUST MISSES.
KIM HAS ONE HIT ON AND THEN
BOUNCES OFF.
CHELSEA HOOKS HER FIRST RING.
KIM HOOKS HER FIRST RING.
KIM HOOKS HER SECOND RING.
ONE RING LEFT.
ONLY WAY TO GUARANTEE YOU SEE
TOMORROW IS TO HAVE IMMUNITY
TONIGHT.
KIM DOES IT!
KIM WINS IMMUNITY!
YOU EARNED IT, KIM.
IT'S ALL YOU.
Jeff: FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY WIN, 30 DAYS IN,
GUARANTEES KIM WILL SEE DAY 31.
AS FOR THE REST YOU, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
I KNOW IT WILL BE AN INTERESTING
AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
TODAY WAS JUST COMPLETE,
UTTER DISAPPOINTMENT, LOSING
LIKE, BOOM.
I WAS BUMMED OUT.
BUT PART OF ME SAID TROY, DON'T
LET YOURSELF GET SO FAR DOWN
WHERE YOU THINK IT'S OVER-OVER.
YOU'RE STILL STANDING.
YOU STILL HAVE A CHANCE TO
SPEAK.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE ODDS ARE.
WELL, I KNOW WHAT THEY ARE.
YOU DON'T.
( LAUGHS )
THEY MUST THINK I HAVE A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
I'M SURELY GOING TO SPLIT THE
VOTE.
NEVER, NEVER SAY DIE.
NOT IN "SURVIVOR."
THIS IS WHAT I'M THINKING, IF
FOR SOME REASON HE PLAYS THE
IDOL, WE THROW TWO VOTES TO
CHRISTINA.
SHE'S USED TO SEEING HER NAME
WRITTEN DOWN.
I THINK IT'S BEEN HAPPENING TO
HER THE WHOLE GAME.
SHE KNOWS EVERYBODY IS NOT CRAZY
ABOUT HER.
ANYBODY ELSE IS GOING TO FLIP.
RIGHT, RIGHT.
AND EVERYONE ELSE VOTES FOR
TROY.
TROY, WE DON'T KNOW IF HE HAS
AN IDOL SO WE HAVE TO SPLIT THE
VOTE BUT I'M GETTING TIRED
EVERYONE IS TELLING ME WHAT TO
DO.
NO ONE THINKS I'M ONE RUNNING
THE SHOW.
EVERYONE THINKS KIM IS.
LIKE, I CAN'T MAKE A DECISION
FOR MYSELF?
LIKE, WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S FRUSTRATING FOR ME.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
SO HOW ARE WE GOING TO DO THE
VOTES?
AND IF YOU JUST WANT TO CONFIRM
IT WITH THEM WE'RE FINE.
YOU'RE SPLITTING.
YEAH, ME AND TARZAN KNOW TO
VOTE FOR YOU, BUT IT'S NOT YOU,
OKAY?
WE'RE JUST PUTTING IT OUT THERE.
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME.
YOU'RE NOT SURE IF HE HAS THE
IDOL.
RIGHT.
AND THEN THE REST OF US WILL
VOTE FOR TROY.
OKAY.
THE PLAN TONIGHT IS TO SPLIT
THE VOTE AND I'M GOING TO STICK
WITH KIM'S PLAN SO I LET
CHRISTINA KNOW WE'RE GOING TO
VOTE YOU AND YOU'RE NOT GOING
HOME.
I SHOULD HAVE JUST THROWN OUT
ANOTHER NAME.
I DON'T WANT HER TO FEEL BAD
BECAUSE PEOPLE DO NOT FORGET HOW
YOU MAKE THEM FEEL.
THE REASON WE DID IT, YOU'RE NOT
SURPRISED SEEING YOUR NAME ONCE,
TWICE, WHATEVER.
YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT AT
ALL.
I DON'T THINK SHE PROCESSED IT
ENOUGH, I MAY BE GOING HOME IF
HE HAS THE IMMUNITY IDOL BUT SHE
WAS FINE WITH IT.
SHE'S GOING TO?
YEAH, SHE SAID NOT TO, LIKE,
FREAK OUT.
ARE YOU OK WITH THAT?
IF I GOT A COUPLE OF VOTES,
ALL HELL WOULD BREAK LOOSE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, CHRISTINA'S
I.Q. IS PROBABLY A 0.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT EVEN
EXISTS.
I MEAN, I'M A SPECIAL ED
TEACHER, SO I HANDLE CHRISTINA
AS ONE OF MY STUDENTS, AND SHE'S
GOING TO DO WHATEVER WE TELL HER
TO DO.
AND IF TROY PULLS OUT AN
IMMUNITY IDOL, CHRISTINA'S GOING
TO GO, AND SHE HAS TO GO, THEN
SHE HAS TO GO.
IT AIN'T MY NAME, SO I DON'T
CARE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
I'M FEELING FINE.
YEAH.
YEAH, I HOPE THAT YOU FEEL
FINE.
YOU ALWAYS FEEL LIKE YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON WITH
THE GIRLS AND STUFF.
I'M ALWAYS, LIKE, SCARED.
THAT'S WHY I'M ALWAYS TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT'S ANYTHING ON
WITH THEM AND FIGURE OUT THEIR
PLACEMENT AND STUFF.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY'RE SAYING
THERE'S STRATEGY BEHIND WHY
THOSE GIRLS WENT THE THREE OF
THEM, AND EVERYTHING?
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE TWO.
YOU HAVE KIM, AND THEN YOU HAVE
CHELSEA.
I DON'T TRUST THE GIRLS 100%.
SO THAT'S WHY I ENTERTAIN THE
IDEA OF TROYZAN'S PROPOSAL
BECAUSE IT MAKES-- IT MAKES
SENSE.
KIM WON, YOU CAN'T VOTE FOR HER.
I NEVER PUT YOUR NAME DOWN, JUST
TO LET YOU OPINION
( LAUGHS )
IF YOU VOTE CHELSEA, I'LL VOTE
CHELSEA.
OKAY.
CHRISTINA SAID SHE WOULD VOTE
FOR CHELSEA, BUT I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY ELSE WOULD VOTE FOR
CHELSEA.
SO NOW I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TRY
TO SOMEHOW FIGURE OUT WHO
THEY'RE SPLITTING THIS VOTE
WITH, AND I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
VOTE FOR THAT PERSON.
I MEAN, THEY'RE OBVIOUSLY GOING
TO SPLIT VOTE BECAUSE THEY DON'T
KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS HAPPENING.
BUT I DON'T THINK ANYBODY KNOWS
HOW THEY REALLY CAN SPLIT THIS
VOTE.
THEY CAN PROBABLY SPLIT IT,
AND THEN THERE'S THE
POSSIBILITY-- BECAUSE I HEARD MY
NAME'S GOING TO BE WRITTEN DOWN
AND EVERYTHING.
AND--
WHEN CHRISTINA SAID WHO
THEY'RE GOING TO SPLIT THE VOTE
WITH-- I'M LIKE, GREAT.
THAT'S EASY.
I STARTED THINKING ABOUT THE
VOTE, HOW IT COULD GO.
I NEED THREE PEOPLE TO JUST VOTE
FOR CHRISTINA AND THEN, BOOM, I
CAN BE THE FOURTH.
AND IT CAN BE A MIRACLE.
SERIOUSLY.
BOOM.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, CHRISTINA'S,
LIKE, GONE, AND THAT WOULD BE
BEAUTIFUL.
IF WE ALL DO WHAT WE SAID
WE'LL DO, TROY WILL GO HOME
TONIGHT.
NOBODY CHANGE THEIR MINDS.
THE PLAN IS TONIGHT TO GIVE
TROY FIVE VOTES AND CHRISTINA
TWO.
I THINK SPLITTING VOTES IS
ALWAYS HARD BECAUSE YOU DON'T
KNOW WHO IS WITH YOU AND WHO IS
NOT SO YOU HAVE FIVE PEOPLE
VOTING FOR TROY.
IF TWO FLIP, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
TROY'S BACK IN THE GAME TONIGHT.
WELL, BUDDY?
WELL, I'M STILL UP FOR GRABS
TODAY.
YOU'RE NOT NECESSARILY GOING
HOME.
I WON'T BELIEVE TROYZAN IS
GOING HOME UNTIL THE MOMENT HE
STANDS IN FRONT JEFF AND JEFF
SNUFFS HIS TORCH.
YOU CAN CONSIDER CHANGING
YOUR MIND ABOUT WHO YOU'RE
VOTING FOR.
DON'T GO WITH KIM AND CHELSEA.
HE'S, LIKE, FULL OF CRAZINESS
AND SURPRISES.
I MEAN, HE'S JUST PLAYING SO
HARD.
WHO KNOWS WHAT'S ABOUT TO
HAPPEN?
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JONAS, MICHAEL, JAY, AND LEIF,
VOTED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SO, STARTED AS MEN VERSUS WOMEN.
IT CERTAINLY APPEARED YET AGAIN
TODAY STILL BE MEN VERSUS WOMEN.
IS THAT WHERE WE'RE AT, TROYZAN?
ARE YOU IN TROUBLE BECAUSE YOU
DO NOT HAVE THE NECKLACE?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S STILL ALL THE WOMEN, PLUS
TARZAN.
AND I'M NOT WEARING THE
NECKLACE, SO WE'LL SEE IF THE
"SURVIVOR" GOD ARE OUT THERE.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
Jeff: SABRINA, IF IT IS MEN
VERSUS WOMEN.
THERE ARE SIX OF YOU.
HAS THERE BEEN MUCH TALK ABOUT
WHO IS NUMBER SIX?
WHO IS NUMBER FIVE?
I WOULDN'T SAY AMONGST ALL
SIX OF US.
IT'S BEEN DROPPED SINCE AT A
TWO, DAY 10, DAY 19.
Jeff: SO CHRISTINA,YOU WHAT
THAT MEANS, RIGHT?
WHAT SHE SAID IS I DON'T THINK
ALL SIX OF US HAVE TALKED ABOUT
IT.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW THERE ARE
CONVERSATIONS WITH OTHER PEOPLE,
AND NO ONE IS REALLY CLEAR ABOUT
WHO IS THE TOP FIVE, TOP FOUR,
TOP THREE.
Jeff: CHELSEA, AGREE WITH
THAT?
NO, I FEEL LIKE THIS GAME
STARTED SO FAST, THAT PEOPLE
WERE THINKING OUT TOP THREE ON
DAY ONE.
BUT SOMETIMES THE PEOPLE WHO
THINK ARE GOING TO BE YOUR TOP
THREE GET VOTED OUT.
PEOPLE CHANGE THEIR MINDS AND
FLIP-FLOP.
THINGS CHANGE.
Jeff: TROYZAN, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE THE KIND OF ANSWER YOU WANT
TO HEAR.
THAT TELLS ME SHE'S NOT
COMPLETELY 100% WITH HER
ALLIANCE.
Jeff: CHRISTINA, WHY ARE
YOU HERE?
WHY AM I HERE?
BECAUSE I'M ONE LUCKY GIRL.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
Jeff: ALICIA, WHY ARE YOU
LAUGHING?
I FIND IT FUNNY THAT WAS HER
ANSWER BECAUSE WHEN WE HAD THE
REWARD CHALLENGE THE GENERAL
CONSENSUS WAS CHRISTINA DOESN'T
DESERVE TO BE HERE.
Jeff: CHRISTINA, WHAT DID
THAT FEEL LIKE?
WELL, THAT REALLY HURT MY
FEELINGS.
I THINK WHAT HAPPENED IN THE
BEGIN IS NO ONE REALLY GOT A
CHANCE TO GET TO KNOW ME.
Jeff: BUT THIS CHALLENGE
WAS JUST TWO DAYS AGO.
RIGHT, I GET THAT.
Jeff: AND THAT'S IMPORTANT,
CHRISTINA, IS A JURY WILL DECIDE
WHO WINS, AND THE JURY HERE OF
THE PEOPLE STILL IN THE GAME,
THINK YOU DON'T DESERVE TO BE
HERE.
I THINK I DESERVE TO BE HERE
JUST AS EVERYBODY ELSE.
I--
BUT I THINK THE GENERAL
CONSENSUS WAS YOU DIDN'T HAVE
ANY STRATEGY THROUGHOUT THE
GAME.
I HAVE BEEN STRATEGIZING
THROUGHOUT THE GAME.
I JUST DON'T TALK ABOUT IT
BECAUSE THE WHOLE GAME IS ABOUT
DECEPTION AND OUTWIT, OUTPLAY,
OUTLAST.
Jeff: TROYZAN, ONCE AGAIN,
MORE GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
NOW CHRISTINA HAS TO DEFEND
HERSELF TO ALICIA, ONE OF THE
SIX WOMEN IN HER ALLIANCE.
OH, YEAH.
EVERYONE KNOWS CHRISTINA'S ON
THE BOTTOM.
THEY'LL NEVER ADMIT THAT.
BUT IT'S JUST FUNNY TO LISTEN TO
THESE LADIES THAT DON'T REALLY
SAY EVERYTHING.
Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
REWARD CHALLENGE.
TROYZAN, YOU WERE PRETTY VOCAL
AT WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS GOING
ON.
OF COURSE.
THERE ARE SIX GIRLS SAYING, I
BELIEVE EVERYBODY, AND WE'RE ALL
BELIEVING EVERYTHING, AND WE'RE
ALL JUST HAPPEN CAMPERS HERE'S."
IF YOU GUYS ARE CRAZY TO BELIEVE
EVERYBODY, GUESS WHAT, I HAVE
OCEAN-FRONT PROPERTY IN KANSAS
I'LL SELL YOU.
Jeff: I'M FROM KANSAS.
THERE IS NO OCEAN-FRONT
PROPERTY.
EXACTLY.
Jeff: KIM, WERE YOU
ENCOURAGED AT ALL HAVING TO PICK
PEOPLE TO GO WITH YOU, WHICH
MEANT OTHER PEOPLE WERE LEFT
OUT?
YEAH.
I MEAN, ABSOLUTELY.
IT WAS KIND OF A LITTLE BIT OF A
NIGHTMARE.
THERE WERE A LOT OF PEOPLE BACK
AT CAMP.
AND, YOU KNOW, TROY'S A
BRILLIANT GUY.
HE KNOWS EXACTLY WHAT TO SAY.
HE'S REALLY SMART.
AND HE'S GOOD AT GETTING INTO
PEOPLE'S HEADS.
Jeff: KAT, YOU WERE
HEARTBROKEN THAT YOU WEREN'T
CHOSEN.
WHY?
I THINK IT WAS BECAUSE OF THE
COMMENT TROY MADE ABOUT KIM
ALICIA AND CHELSEA.
THAT'S THE TOP THREE RIGHT
THERE.
AND I THOUGHT AM I A WEAK
PLAYER?
AM A FOLLOWER?
AM I SO FAR UP KELSEY AND KIM'S
ASS THAT I CAN'T MAKE A DECISION
FOR MYSELF.
I DON'T WANT TO GO DOWN AS A
WEAK PLAYER OR A FOLLOWER.
SO HE GOT TO ME.
Jeff: TROYZAN AS WE GET
READY TO VOTE, IT'S PRETTY CLEAR
IT'S YOU OR SOMEBODY ELSE.
YOUR JOB TODAY WAS TO MAKE IT
SOMEBODY ELSE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING RIGHT NOW?
I FEEL PRETTY GOOD.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CANNOT
VOTE FOR KIM.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CHELSEA, YOU'RE UP.
I AM HOPING THAT YOU
GET A LOT OF VOTES
PLEASE, GO HOME
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE TIME TO DO
SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, CHELSEA.
TROY.
THAT'S THREE VOTES TROY.
ONE VOTE CHELSEA.
CHRISTINA.
THAT'S TWO VOTES CHRISTINA.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES CHRISTINA, THREE
VOTES TROY, ONE VOTE CHELSEA.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FIFTH MEMBER OF THE JURY,
TROY.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DO IT.
Jeff: TROYZAN, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, IT HAS BEEN THE MISSION OF
THIS GROUP TO GET RID OF
TROYZAN.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
NOW WHAT?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
SURVIVOR.
TARZAN IS THE LAST MAN STANDING
BUT CAN THE WOMEN KEEP IT
TOGETHER?
I AM SO MAD RIGHT NOW.
DEFINITELY ENOUGH REASON TO VOTE
OFF KAT.
SABRINA HAS NO IDEA THAT HER
ASS IS ON THE LINE.
THAT'S WHY A BLINDSIDE IS SO
GREAT.
EVERYONE IS WANTING KAT OUT
NEXT.
SABRINA FIRST.
FROM HERE ON OUT, IT'S GOING
TO BE A CAT FIGHT.
THE LAST 11 YEARS I'VE BEEN
THINKING I'M GOING TO GET ON
"SURVIVOR" AND MY ONLY OBJECTIVE
IS TO BE THE WINNER AND I'M A
BIT SAD THAT I DIDN'T REACH MY
GOAL.
DEFINITELY THE ODDS WERE AGAINST
ME.
IT WAS SEVEN ON ONE.
BUT I DID WHAT I COULD DO.
I PLAYED EXACTLY WHO I AM.
THE FANS OUT THERE I KNOW ARE
GOING TO LOVE MY GAME AND THEY
WILL APPRECIATE IT.