Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
KIM AND THE WOMEN HAVE TAKEN OUT
THE MEN SYSTEMATICALLY SINCE THE
MERGE LEAVING TROYZAN
OUTNUMBERED ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK.
WITH HIS BACK AGAINST THE WALL,
TROYZAN NEEDED TO WIN IMMUNITY.
TROYZAN COMES UP A LITTLE SHORT.
TARZAN REALLY TAKING HIS TIME.
TARZAN MOVES ON, TROYZAN IS OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
THE WOMEN BELIEVED TROYZAN MIGHT
HAVE ANOTHER HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND DECIDED TO SPLIT THEIR
VOTE.
IT'S BEST TO BE SMART, WE
THROW TWO VOTES AT CHRISTINA.
Jeff: TROYZAN GOT WIND OF
THE PLAN WHEN CHRISTINA SPILLED
THE BEANS.
I HEARD MY NAME WILL BE
WRITTEN DOWN.
WHEN CHRISTINA SAID WHO
THEY'RE GOING TO SPLIT THE VOTE
WITH I'M LIKE GREAT, THAT'S WHAT
I NEED TO HEAR.
Jeff: NEEDING ONLY ONE MORE
PERSON TO SHIFT THE VOTES
AGAINST CHRISTINA, TROYZAN
APPEALED TO KAT.
YOU ARE ON THE BOTTOM.
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER CHANGING
YOUR MIND ABOUT WHO YOU'RE
VOTING FOR.
NEVER SAY DIE.
NOT IN "SURVIVOR."
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
CHRISTINA WAS ON THE HOT SEAT.
THERE ARE SIX WOMEN.
HAS THEREIN THERE BEEN MUCH TALK
ABOUT WHO IS NUMBER SIX?
I WOULDN'T SAY AMONGST ALL
SIX OF US.
THE GENERAL CONSENSUS WAS YOU
DIDN'T HAVE STRATEGY.
I HAVE BEEN STRATEGIZING
THROUGHOUT THE GAME.
I JUST DON'T TALK ABOUT IT.
Jeff: IN THE END... THE
11th PERSON VOTING OUT AND
FIFTH MEMBER OF THE JURY,
TROYZAN WAS THE FIFTH MAN BUT
DELIVERED A MESSAGE TO KAT
BEFORE HE LEFT.
DO IT.
Jeff: IT HAS BEEN THE
MISSION OF THIS GROUP TO GET RID
OF TROYZAN.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
SEVEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
LIKE THAT WAS YOUR FINAL
WORD?
IT'S REALLY GOOD THAT TROY IS
GONE.
I, LIKE, PHYSICALLY FEEL
RELIEVED.
LIKE, I FEEL, LIKE... YOU KNOW
WHEN YOU HAVE A PIT IN YOUR
STOMACH AND IT GOES AWAY?
THAT'S HOW I FEEL NOW THAT TROY
IS GONE.
HOW DID YOU GET THREE VOTES?
TROY PLAYED HER.
TROY SWITCHED HIS VOTE?
YUP.
YOU COULD HAVE POTENTIALLY
WENT HOME TODAY.
I KNOW I COULD HAVE.
TRIBAL TONIGHT JUST SHOWED
HOW STUPID CHRISTINA IS.
SEEING CHRISTINA ANSWER THE
QUESTIONS IN FRONT OF THE JURY
MADE HER LOOK DUMB WHEREAS
SABRINA ACTUALLY CAN TALK AND
SHE CAN SWAY THEM THE MORE SHE'S
LEFT HERE.
THE WHOLE TIME JONAS WAS
LOOKING AT CHRISTIE THAT LIKE
"WHY IS THIS GIRL STILL HERE?"
THE MORE CHRISTIE THAT OPENS HER
MOUTH AT TRIBAL COUNCIL IT'S SO
MUCH BETTER THAN HAVING SABRINA
THERE.
NOW IT'S JUST US GIRLS AND
TARZAN AND HE'S REALLY NOT A
THREAT.
BUT SABRINA SCARES ME SO I
PERSONALLY DON'T WANT HER HERE.
SO I'M NOT WORRIED.
I THINK I'M SITTING IN A PERFECT
SPOT.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE HAVE SAID THAT
I'M THE MISFIT OR THAT I'M AT
THE BOTTOM AND LITTLE DO THEY
KNOW I'M AT THE TOP CONTROLLING
EVERYTHING.
I'M THE MOST POWERFUL PLAYER IN
THIS GAME.
TREEMAIL!
(SCREAMING)
SPRINT, I LOVE YOU!
OH, MY GOD!
SO SABRINA AND I GET TREEMAIL
AND WHEN I LIFTED THE BOX AND
SAW "SPRINT" I ALREADY KNEW WHAT
WAS HAPPENING.
GATHER EVERYONE AROUND.
COME CLOSER.
WE HAVE TO PUT TOGETHER A
FREAKING PUZZLE.
PSYCH!
STOP SHAKING IT!
WE HAVE VIDEO MAIL!
OH, MY GOSH!
"YOU'VE BEEN LIVING A LIFE
WITHOUT LIMITS AND SIMPLICITY
PROVIDES YOUR POWER.
WHEN SPONTANEOUS DECISIONS BREED
SUCCESS, IT'S MORE THAN FOOD YOU
SHALL DEVOUR."
OH, MY GOD!
SHH!
YOU HAVE TO BE VERY QUIET!
HELLO, SABRINA.
(SCREAMING)
YOU'RE ON THE ISLAND.
YOUR ABSENCE IS A VOID IN
EVERYONE'S HEART.
TODAY WE GOT TREEMAIL FROM
SPRINT.
I NEVER THOUGHT SPRINT COULD BE
SO GOOD TO ME AND IT WAS MY
BROTHER WHO CAME ALL THE WAY OUT
TO THE ISLAND.
HOPEFULLY I'LL GET TO SEE HIM
AND SPEND TIME WITH HIM TODAY.
HI, SISTER!
OH!
ALL I HAVE TO SAY IS YOU
BETTER WIN THE NEXT CHALLENGE
BECAUSE I HAD TO WORK TWO
DOUBLES TO MAKE THIS TRIP
HAPPEN.
I'M SUPER PROUD OF YOU.
I LOVE YOU AND I HOPE YOU'RE
DOING WELL.
HEY, CHELSEA!
CAME A LONG WAY DOWN HERE TO SEE
YOU ON THIS ISLAND.
IT'S GORGEOUS.
HOPE YOU'RE DOING WELL.
EVERYBODY BACK HOME IS SAYING
HOW MUCH THEY LOVE YOU AND MISS
YOU.
WE THINK ABOUT YOU ALL THE TIME.
I LOVE MY DAD.
HI, CHRISTINA.
OH, MY GOD, MY DAD.
I HOPE YOU'RE DOING WELL AND
I HOPE THAT YOU'RE NOT SUFFERING
AS MUCH AS I AM.
MY DAD JUST GOT A KIDTY
TRANSPLANT LAST YEAR.
HE ONLY HAS ABOUT FIVE TO TEN
YEARS TO LIVE.
HE'S ONLY 53 AND I WANT TO DO SO
MUCH FOR HIM AND, YES, IT'S
URGENT.
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE WHATEVER I'M
DOING RIGHT NOW IS NEVER ENOUGH
AND I NEED TO DO MORE.
I LOVE YOU AND I AM VERY
PROUD OF YOU.
HI, KIM.
I'M HERE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
I'M SO, SO PROUD OF YOU AND I
WANT YOU TO KNOW HOW MUCH I LOVE
YOU.
I'M HOPING TO SPEND TIME WITH
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
YEAH!
KAT, WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I ACTUALLY MADE IT HERE.
I'M SO EXCITED TO SEE YOU.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN DOING SO GOOD.
I GOT TO SEE MY COUSIN WHO'S
MY BEST FRIEND AND THE MOST
IMPORTANT PERSON IN MY WHOLE
LIFE.
AND WE REALLY CAN'T WAIT TO
SEE YOU.
TARZAN.
YEAH, TARZAN.
HI TWEETY, HOW'S MY TARZAN
DOING?
TO SEE MY WIFE ON THE SPRINT
PHONE REMINDS ME OF WHAT A
TREASURE SHE IS IN MY LIFE.
I DON'T DESERVE HER.
SOMEHOW I GOT HER.
GOD BLESSED ME WITH HER.
JUST A WONDERFUL THING FOR US TO
BE ABLE TO LIVE TOGETHER TILL WE
DO.
MY BED IS AWFUL LONELY.
SURE MISS YOU A WHOLE LOT.
LOVE YOU.
SHE'S HERE!
THERE'S PEOPLE THAT NEED TO
SEE THEIR FAMILY BECAUSE THEY
MAY NOT HAVE THAT MUCH LONGER
HERE ON THIS EARTH.
TARZAN IS IN A 30-YEAR MARRIAGE,
HE'S 64, THEY DON'T HAVE
CHILDREN.
IT'S JUST... I HOPE THE OTHER
WOMEN ARE THINKING LIKE THAT AND
NOT BEING TOO SELFISH AND SO
IT'S KIND OF LIKE I'M PLAYING
FOR ME AND TARZAN TODAY.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, THIS MORNING IN
TREEMAIL YOU RECEIVED THE EVO 3D
FROM SPRINT.
I'LL GET IT BACK, ALICIA.
THANK YOU.
SO, TARZAN, DID OFF VIDEO
MESSAGE FROM TERI, YOUR WIFE?
YES, I FEEL HER SPIRIT NOW
THAT SHE'S ON THIS ISLAND.
Jeff: SO THE ONLY THING
THAT WOULD MAKE THIS DAY BETTER
IS IF THEY WERE ALL RIGHT HERE
IN PERSON.
YEAH.
Jeff: AND THEY ARE.
KIM, HERE'S YOUR SISTER BETH.
OH, MY GOSH!
KIM, WHAT'S THE FEELING WHEN YOU
HUG SOMEONE WHO YOU KNOW IS
TRULY SAFE?
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
BETH IS MY OLDER SISTER, SHE'S
BEEN A SECOND MOM TO ME MY WHOLE
LIFE.
SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND IN THE
WHOLE WORLD AND SHE'S THE MOST
REAL PERSON I'VE EVER KNOWN.
SHE TAKES GOOD CARE OF ME.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS TAKE
A SPOT OVER HERE.
CHRISTINA, WHO WAS YOUR VIDEO
MESSAGE FROM?
FROM MY DAD.
HE JUST HAD A KIDNEY TRANSPLANT
LAST YEAR SO I ALWAYS WORRY
ABOUT HIS WELL-BEING.
KNOWING THAT, YOU KNOW, MY DAD
MAY NOT BE AROUND FOR ANOTHER
FIVE, TEN YEARS IS JUST... THIS
EXPERIENCE MEANS SO MUCH TO ME.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CHRISTINA,
LET'S BRING YOUR DAD OUT.
HERE'S CHRISTINA'S FATHER.
OH, HE'S NOT MESSING AROUND.
HE'S RUNNING.
HI, DADDY!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
OH, I MISSED YOU.
I MISSED YOU, TOO!
Jeff: SUNG, HAVE YOU BEEN
WORRIED ABOUT CHRISTINA?
CLEARLY YOU ADORE HER.
YEAH, I MISHER DEARLY BUT I
KNEW SHE COULD HANG IN THERE.
SHE SETS HER GOAL AND SHE'S LIKE
A PIT BULL.
Jeff: CHRISTINA, WHAT HAS
CHANGED ABOUT HOW YOU SEE YOUR
DAD?
I FEEL GUILTY THAT I DON'T
VISIT HIM ENOUGH.
I WISH I COULD SEE HIM SO MUCH
MORE.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS FAMILY.
I CAN'T BE AWAY FROM HIM.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS TAKE
YOUR SPOT OVER HERE.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
CHELSEA, HERE'S YOUR DAD KEN.
DADDY!
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
HOW'D YOU GET SO TAN?
IT'S DIRT, IT'S NOT TAN.
IT'S DIRT.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
Jeff: CHELSEA, YOU CAN'T
GET ENOUGH.
I KNOW.
I'VE BEEN LIKE A HARD ASS ON THE
SHOW, BUT THIS IS MY SOFT SPOT
RIGHT HERE.
Jeff: AFTER 31 DAYS OF
BEING THE TOUGH WOMAN OUT HERE,
I THINK WHAT EVERYBODY IS SEEING
RIGHT NOW IS THE LITTLE GIRL.
REALLY?
Jeff: YOUR FACE LOOKS
DIFFERENT.
I'M SO HAPPY.
Jeff: TAKE A SPOT.
SABRINA, HERE'S YOUR BROTHER
TONY.
COME ON OUT, TONY.
OH!
WOW!
Jeff: HE'S SPRINTING.
LET ME SEE YOU, OH, MY GOD!
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
Jeff: TONY, HAVE YOU BEEN
WORRIED ABOUT HER?
I KNOW SHE'S TOUGH AND
RESILIENT BUT THIS IS AMAZING.
SHE'S TRULY A SOLDIER.
WHAT I LOVE MOST ABOUT HIM IS
THAT HE PUTS ME BEFORE HIMSELF
AND THAT'S WHAT A BIG BROTHER IS
SUPPOSED TO DO AND, UM, THIS IS
PRICELESS RIGHT HERE.
JUST THIS RIGHT HERE.
Jeff: ALICIA, HERE'S YOUR
SISTER LETICIA.
COME ON OUT.
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR RELATIONSHIP.
I'M SURE SHE'S STRUGGLING
WITH HER EMOTIONS RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE WE AREN'T AN EMOTIONAL
FAMILY.
WE EXPRESS OUR AFFECTION IN A
DIFFERENT WAY.
WE'RE VERY SAR CAST WICK EACH
OTHER.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I'M SO,
SO, SO PROUD OF YOU.
Jeff: KAT, ARE YOU READY TO
SEE YOUR WASSEN?
I'M READY TO SEE HIM.
Jeff: ROCK ROBBY, COME ON
OUT.
IT'S KAT'S COUSIN.
OH, MY GOD!
HOW DID... OH WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
(LAUGHTER)
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT SHE'S
SAYING.
Jeff: I THINK THEY'RE
SPEAKING THEIR OWN LANGUAGE.
(LAUGHTER)
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
HE'S THE ONE THAT PUSHES ME
EVERYDAY.
WE WORK TOGETHER, WE LIVE
TOGETHER, WE BREATHE TOGETHER.
HE'S THE MOST IMPORTANT PERSON
IN MY LIFE!
AND HE'S HERE ON THIS ISLAND
WITH ME!
HILARIOUS!
TARZAN!
Jeff: WOW!
Jeff: LET'S BRING OUT YOUR
WIFE TERI.
TERI, COME ON OUT.
LET'S SEE WHO MARRIED THIS CRAZY
GUY WHO CALLS HIMSELF TARZAN.
I'M SORRY.
Jeff: TERI, HOW'S LIFE
DIFFERENT WITHOUT TARZAN AROUND?
IT'S BEEN 31 DAYS YOU'VE BEEN
WITHOUT HIM.
VERY LONELY.
HE'S MY EVERYTHING.
YOU TAKE HIM AWAY, I'M LOST.
Jeff: ME TOO, SWEETIE.
Jeff: TARZAN, HOW HAVE YOU
STAYED CONNECTED TO TERI OUT
HERE?
WE'RE SOUL MATES.
WE HAVE A QUANTUM ENTANGLEMENT.
Jeff: I COULD HAVEN'T PUT
IT ANY BETTER.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, JOINED THE REST
OF THE LOVED ONES.
HI, TERI!
Jeff: LET'S GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE.
SURVIVORS, YOU WILL BE ATTACHED
TO A ROPE THAT IS WOVEN THROUGH
A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
ON MY GO YOU WILL RACE TO
UNTANGLE THAT ROPE AND MAKE YOUR
WAY THROUGH THE COURSE.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
YES!
Jeff: YOU AND YOUR LOVED
ONE WILL GO TO A BEAUTIFUL SPOT
WHERE YOU WILL ENJOY FISH,
CHICKEN, BEEF KEBOBS,
MARGARITAS.
THIS WILL BE A CHANCE FOR YOU TO
SHARE A ONCE IN A LIFETIME
EXPERIENCE WITH YOUR LOVED ONE.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
YES!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ONE MORE
TWIST.
YOUR LOVED ONES WILL BE ATTACHED
TO YOU.
OH, I KNEW THAT.
YOU WILL BE RUNNING IT
TOGETHER.
WE GOT IT!
Jeff: WE'LL GET YOU PAIRED
UP AND GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR AN AFTERNOON WITH YOUR LOVED
ONES, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ROPE MANAGEMENT IS KEY IN THIS.
YOU NEED SLACK.
ONCE YOU FIGURE OUT HOW TO USE
THE SLACK YOU'LL FIGURE OUT THE
KEY TO THIS CHALLENGE.
PULL IT!
COME ON!
KIM AND BETH GETTING THROUGH
THE FIRST OBSTACLE.
CHRISTINA AND SUNG GETTING
THROUGH IT.
OH, GOD!
Jeff: ALICIA AND LETICIA
ARE THERE N THERE.
KAT AND ROBBY MOVING.
KEN IS THROUGH.
IT'S IN A KNOT, TONY!
Jeff: BROTHER AND SISTER
STRUGGLING.
KIM AND BETH ATTACKING THE
COURSE.
CHELSEA AND HER DAD ARE WORKING
TOGETHER WELL.
WE'RE IN IT, DADDY.
COME ON!
Jeff: KAT, ALICIA, CHELSEA
AND KIM ALONG WITH THEIR LOVED
ONES ARE IN THE LEAD.
BIG REWARD AND EVERYBODY WANTS
IT.
KAT AND ROBBY NOW STARTING TO
PULL AHEAD.
KIM AND BETH GOT TO PICK IT UP.
ALICIA, YOU'VE GOT TO GET
MOVING.
DAMN!
Jeff: SABRINA AND TONY
COMPLETELY OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: TARZAN, YOU NEED TO
PICK IT UP IF YOU WANT TO SPEND
TIME WITH YOUR WIFE.
CHRISTINA AND HER DAD DOING
THEIR BEST BUT THEY'RE FALLING
BEHIND.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE AND IT'S
VERY CLOSE.
KIM AND HER SISTER, CHELSEA AND
HER DAD, KAT AND HER COUSIN.
DUDE, COME ON!
Jeff: KAT AND ROBBY GETTING
CAUGHT UP IN THOSE LAST FEW BITS
OF ROPE.
THE DOOR IS OPEN NEW.
KIM AND BETH ARE NOW WORKING IT.
CHELSEA AND HER DAD ARE NOW BACK
IN IT.
IF YOU WANT TO SPEND TIME WITH
YOUR LOVED ONE, YOU'VE GOT TO
MOVE.
KAT AND ROBBY HAVE FIGURED IT
OUT.
GOT TO GET TO THE FINISH RIGHT
HERE.
VERY CLOSE.
KEEP MOVING!
KIM AND BETH ARE RIGHT THERE.
IT'S NECK IN NECK!
KIM IS THROUGH.
KAT IS THROUGH, ROBBY'S GOT TO
GET THROUGH.
KAT AND KIM, WHO'S GOING TO GET
TO THE FINISH FIRST.
COME ON!
MOVE!
Jeff: VERY CLOSE, MOVE,
BETH!
LET'S GO, ROBBY.
Jeff: COME ON!
KAT AND ROBBY WIN THE REWARD.
(SCREAMING)
I WON ONE, GUYS!
COME ON, I WON ONE!
Jeff: KAT AND ROBBY, COME
ON OVER HERE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Jeff: SO AN AFTERNOON AWAY
FROM CAMP.
CHOOSE ONE SURVIVOR AND THEIR
LOVED ONE TO JOIN YOU FOR THE
AFTERNOON.
UM, KIM.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: EVEN THOUGH KYM
DIDN'T CHOOSE KAT LAST TIME, KAT
IS CHOOSING KIM THIS TIME.
KAT, ONE MORE PERSON TO CHOOSE.
UM... ALICIA.
Jeff: ALICIA, WHO ALSO WENT
ON THE LAST WE WARD WITHOUT KAT.
NOW, HERE'S THE THING, I HAVE
AN EXPLANATION.
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO HANG OUT
WITH THESE TWO GIRLS FOR A VERY
LONG TIME.
JUST US AND HAVE A GREAT... AND
ALCOHOL.
I MEAN, MARGARITAS!
OH, MY GOD!
I'M ABOUT TO GET DRUNK.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KAT, KIM,
ALICIA.
THE EVO 3D FROM SPRINT.
WITH THAT YOU CAN RECORD SOME
MEMORIES, TAKE SOME VIDEOS, TAKE
SOME PHOTOS.
FOR THE REST OF YOU, TIME TO SAY
GOOD-BYE TO YOUR LOVED ONES.
YOU DON'T HAVE LONG, ALL
RIGHT?
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
BYE, GUYS.
HAVE FUN.
GOD, SHE SHOULD HAVE PICKED
YOU, TARZAN.
TARZAN AND CHRISTINA SHOULD HAVE
BEEN THE ONES TO GO.
CHRISTINA, TARZAN, CHELSEA,
GRAB YOUR STUFF HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GUYS, YOU SHOULD HAVE A FUN
AFTERNOON.
GET OUT OF HERE, GO ENJOY IT.
I FELT LIKE THAT WAS A REALLY
SELFISH DECISION FOR KAT NOT TO
TAKE TARZAN AND CHRISTINA.
I DON'T KNOW HOW ANGRY THEY'RE
GOING TO BE BUT I'M GOING TO
HAVE DO MAJOR DAMAGE CONTROL
BACK AT CAMP.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, LUNCH
IS READY NOW.
HELP YOURSELF.
I FEEL LIKE A WON THE BEST
REWARD.
LIKE, I WON!
YOU SEE ME AT THIS CHALLENGE?
IT'S LIKE, YES, I WON SOMETHING!
AND I REALLY DESERVED TO WIN,
DANG IT!
I HAVEN'T WON ANYTHING!
I REALLY JUST WANTED TO SPEND
TIME WITH KIM AND ALICIA ON A
GENUINE FRIENDSHIP LEVEL.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T HAVE PICKED
THOSE TWO PEOPLE STRATEGICALLY
BUT I DID AND YOU CAN'T GO BACK
ON IT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
AM I GOING TO DWELL ON IT?
NO, I'LL EAT MY CAKE, GET DRUNK
AND GO BACK TO THE TRIBE AND
DEAL WITH THEM LATER.
IT'S GOOD TO FINALLY MEET
Y'ALL.
US THREE, DAY ONE IT WAS
ALREADY DONE.
UH-HUH.
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
SO OUR WHOLE TRIBE WAS ALL
WOMEN, NOW WE HAVE SIX GIRLS
LEFT.
WE ELIMINATED ALL THE GUYS.
RIGHT NOW SERVE SO IN CHECK.
TARZAN IS IN CHECK.
SABRINA IS IN CHECK, THAT'S WHY
I THINK WE SHOULD TAKE OUT
SABRINA BEFORE CHRISTINA BECAUSE
CHRISTINA KNOWS THE DEAL.
THIS REWARD IS THE ONE TIME
WE WERE ABLE TO FINALLY TALK
ABOUT OUR FINAL THREE.
DO I BELIEVE THIS IS THE FINAL
THREE?
YES.
DO I WANT TO JINX IT NO?
NO, I'M NOT GOING TO SPEAK ABOUT
IT.
IT'S A SERIOUSLY CONFIDENTIAL
SITUATION.
THE LONGER I DO THIS THE MORE
I THINK THIS IS MY BEST OPTION.
THESE GUYS?
UH-HUH.
TO WIN.
I DON'T THINK ALICIA WILL GET
MANY VOTES.
SHE'S NOT WELL LIKED.
BUT SHE'S DELUSIONAL ABOUT THAT
AND KAT, SHE WOULD BE THE PERSON
THAT WOULD HAVE A SHOW LIKE HOW
A MILLION DOLLARS RUIN MID-LIFE
IN A YEAR AND SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHERE SHE SPENT THE MONEY.
MY WHOLE PLOY TO BOTH OF THEM IS
YOU'RE GOING TO KICK MY ASS IN
THE END BUT I WOULD BE REALLY
SURPRISED IF THERE'S ANYBODY
THAT YOU FEEL THAT WAY ABOUT I
WOULD SAY STAKE WITH THEM.
FINAL THREE TALK IS HAPPENING
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
WE HAVE TO DO VIDEOS.
DO IT!
I FEEL LIKE THIS MAY BE MY
BEST OPTION TO GO WITH KAT AND
ALICIA WHO I FEEL LIKE I CAN
BE... THEY WANT TO VOTE OFF
SABRINA BUT I'VE HAD AN ALLIANCE
WITH SABRINA SINCE THE BEGINNING
SO I WOULD BE VOTING OUT SOMEONE
THAT I WAS PREVIOUSLY IN THE TOP
THREE WITH.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY IF I
DON'T THINK I CAN WIN AGAINST
SABRINA THAT WOULD BE STUPID TO
TAKE HER TO THE FINAL THREE WITH
ME.
DUDE, I AM SO MAD RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, HONESTLY, IF KAT WOULD
HAVE PICKED ME I WOULD HAVE SAID
NO, TARZAN'S GOING.
I WOULD HAVE SWITCHED OUT.
NO DOUBT IN MY MIND YOU TWO
SHOULD HAVE WENT.
PERIOD.
WHAT IT WAS, IT WAS TOTALLY
SELFISH.
TRUE.
MAYBE IF I BEGGED SHE WOULD
HAVE TAKEN ME.
NO.
I DON'T THINK SHE WOULD HAVE
TAKEN YOU.
THAT'S HOW SHE IS.
I WOULD HAVE PICKED TARZAN.
THAT'S JUST THE OBVIOUS CHOICE.
BECAUSE THIS MAN NEEDS TO SEE
HIS WIFE, PERIOD.
THEN CHRISTINA BECAUSE OF THE
KIDNEY TRANSPLANT, HER DAD MAY
HAVE A COUPLE YEARS LEFT.
SO THAT REALLY PISSED ME OFF.
KAT IS A BRATTY 23-YEAR-OLD WHO
DOESN'T DESERVE TO GO TO THE
END.
THIS IS DEFINITELY ENOUGH REASON
TO MAKE ME VOTE OFF KAT.
YEAH.
EASILY.
I THINK SHE'S IN THE FIRING
LINE BUT I THINK SHE'S AT THE
END OF THE FIRING LINE.
THAT'S UP TO US, THOUGH,
TARZAN.
WHEN WE WANT HER OFF.
WHAT IF ME, CHRISTINA,
SABRINA, KIM AND YOU WANT KAT
OUT?
WELL, IF THAT WERE THE CASE,
THAT WOULD THAT WOULD BE AN
ERROR BECAUSE KAT IS NOT A
THINKER.
I THINK THAT PEOPLE THAT ARE
THINKING WOULD LEAVE HER IN HERE
LONGER KNOWING FULL WELL THAT AT
ANY TIME IS...
IT'S BASICALLY HER SOCIAL
GAME WITH ALL THE GUYS.
THAT...
IS THAT WHAT WORRIES YOU?
THAT WORRIES ME.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
KAT SCREWED UP NOW THE TARGET
IS ON HER BACK.
PLUS I DON'T THINK ANYONE WANTS
TO GO TO THE END WITH KAT
BECAUSE LAST TRIBAL TROY
WHISPERED IN HER EAR "YOU CAN DO
IT.
"SO THAT'S MAKING US ALL A
LITTLE NERVOUS.
NERVOUS.
HOW ARE WE GOING TO GET EVERYONE
TO VOTE KAT?
ALL WE NEED IS FOUR.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
TALKING WITH KIM WHEN SHE GETS
BACK.
I JUST HOPE WE AGREE THAT KAT IS
A SMART PERSON TO TAKE OUT NEXT.
WHEN WE GOT BACK HERE THERE
WERE SOME PISSED OFF PEOPLE.
EVERYONE'S WANTING KAT OUT NEXT.
THEY'RE GOING TO WANT SABRINA
FIRST.
ALICIA AND KAT?
I SPENT THE DAY WITH THESE
TWO AND THEY THINK WE'RE A
THREAT.
THAT'S HOW DUMB THEY ARE.
SAB IS NOT DUMB.
THEY'RE DUMB.
SO YOU THINK SAB TONIGHT?
I THINK IT'S OUR BEST PLAN.
OKAY.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GO TO THE
END WITH KAT.
I'M THINKING IT'S IMMUNITY
TODAY AND WE HAVE DECIDED
SABRINA IS GOING HOME FOR SURE.
I DO THINK SHE HAS A GOOD SHOT
OF
GETTING A LOT OF JURY VOTES
BECAUSE SHE'S PERSUASIVE.
SO IT'S SO IMPORTANT WHO WINS
BECAUSE WE HAVE A PLAN AND IF
SOMEBODY WINS IMMUNITY THAT WAS
SUPPOSED TO GO HOME IT'S GOING
TO BE CHAOS.
DID I MISS ANYTHING?
NO.
WE JUST NEED TO SEE WHO WINS
IMMUNITY.
SABRINA BETTER NOT PULL OUT A
SUPERSTAR ACT.
I THINK AT SOME POINT IN THIS
GAME I STARTED TO THINK, WELL,
MAYBE IT'S NOT SMART IF I WIN
IMMUNITY BUT I DON'T KNOW IF
I'LL EVER FEEL SAFE SO I'VE JUST
DECIDED AT THIS POINT IF I CAN
TAKE EVERY IMMUNITY FROM HERE ON
OUT I WILL.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
KIM, GOT TO GIVE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE BULL
STANDING ON A LEDGE OVER THE
WATER.
YOU'LL BE HOLDING ON THE A
HANDLE BEHIND YOUR BACK.
THAT HANDLE IS ATTACHED TO A
WINCH.
EVERY TIME I CRANK IT, IT WILL
LOWER YOU CLOSER TO THE WATER.
WHEN THE STRAIN BECOMES TOO MUCH
TO HOLD ON ANY LONGER, YOU'LL
FALL IN THE WATER AND OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY.
GUARANTEED.
ONE IN SIX SHOT AT WINNING THIS
GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
EVERYBODY READY?
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
GOT TO KEEP YOUR FEET IN BETWEEN
THE PAINT AND POINTED FORWARD.
YOU HAVE TO HOLD ON TO THE BAR
BEHIND YOU ABOVE YOUR HIPS.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY'S IN PLACE.
YOU READY TO GET LOWERED A
LITTLE BIT?
OH, BOY.
OH, GOD.
Jeff: HERE WE GO.
EVERY TIME I MOVE THIS, THAT BAR
LETS OUT A LITTLE MORE ROPE AND
YOU FALL CLOSER TO THAT WATER.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: THAT'S GOING TO ADD A
LITTLE MORE STRESS NOW.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS HOLD ON.
THAT'S IT.
JUST HANG ON LONGER THAN
EVERYBODY ELSE.
BEEN UP THERE TEN MINUTES.
PROBABLY SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
UP THERE AN HOUR ALREADY.
TARZAN STRUGGLING A LITTLE BIT.
SABRINA STEPPED OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
GO AHEAD AND DROP IN THE WATER.
SABRINA FIRST OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO SIX.
TARZAN IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE
AND WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE WOMEN
STILL FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY,
WOULD LOVE TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT WITH THAT
NECKLACE.
NO MATTER HOW CONFIDENT YOU FEEL
IN YOUR ALLIANCE, YOU ARE CRAZY
IF YOU THINK YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY
SAFE.
I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
I'M DONE, GUYS, HAVE FUN.
Jeff: ALICIA STEPS OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE AND WE ARE DOWN TO
FOUR.
FOUR PEOPLE FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY ON DAY 33.
YOU ARE HAVING TO EARN IT RIGHT
HERE.
DIG DEEP.
I CAN'T DO IT.
MY FINGERS ARE SLIPPING.
OH, GOD.
GOOD JOB, CHELSEA.
Jeff: CHELSEA OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE AND WE ARE DOWN TO
THREE: KAT, KIM, CHRISTINA.
CHRISTINA CONTEMPLATING CAN I
STICK IN A LITTLE LONGER OR
SHOULD I STEP OFF?
I'M GOING TO JUMP.
MY FINGER'S KILLING ME.
GOOD LUCK, GIRLS.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: CHRISTINA IS OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
SIDE BY SIDE.
KAT AND KIM.
BOTH WOMEN REALLY DIGGING DEEP.
BEEN UP HERE ONE HOUR.
YOU'VE BEEN HANGING.
WOW.
Jeff: PERFECT TIME TO MAKE
IT A LITTLE MORE DIFFICULT.
HERE WE GO.
IT LOOKS SO INCREMENTAL VISUALLY
BUT I KNOW WHAT KIND OF PRESSURE
THAT'S ADDING TO YOUR BODY.
ALICIA, IMPRESSIVE BATTLE?
VERY.
I DIDN'T KNOW KIM HAD IT IN HER.
YEAH.
VERY IMPRESSED.
I JUST WANT TO WIN THIS ONE.
KIM WINS ALL OF THEM.
Jeff: KIM HASN'T MOVED
SINCE THIS CHALLENGE BEGAN.
COME ON, KIM!
WOW.
Jeff: KAT FALLS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
KIM WINS HER SECOND INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
GOOD JOB.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
WOW.
CAREFUL, KAT, ARE YOU OKAY?
HEY.
YOU AIN'T GONNA HIGH FIVE HE?
NO.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: KIM, NICE JOB.
WHY, THANK YOU.
IMPRESSIVE.
(APPLAUSE)
KIM SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL ONCE AGAIN AND AFTER 33
VERY TOUGH DAYS IN THIS GAME ONE
OF YOU GOING HOME TONIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
I WILL SEE YOU GUYS AT TRIBAL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND GET BACK TO
CAMP. CONGRATS.
I'M GLAD KIM WON IMMUNITY BUT
I'M NOT SURE SABRINA SHOULD BE
THE NEXT TO GO.
I THINK KAT, JUST HER
SELFISHNESS THROUGHOUT THIS
WHOLE GAME
SO SHE SHOULD BE NEXT
TO GO
THERE'S STILL A LOT OF TALKING
THAT NEEDS TO GO ON.
I COMMEND Y'ALL FOR STAYING
THAT LONG.
THAT WAS PRETTY BRUTAL.
ARE YOU HURTING?
YEAH.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
KICKING YOUR ASS.
I'M REALLY UPSET ABOUT THE
CHALLENGE.
I MEAN, TO LOSE TO SOMEONE WHO'S
28 YEARS OLD WHO'S SIX YEARS
OLDER THAN ME?
IT'S LIKE HOW EMBARRASSING IS
THAT?
DON'T GET ME WRONG, I LOVE HER
MORE THAN ANYTHING IN THE WORLD
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF I'M EVER
GOING TO BE ABLE TO BEAT HER IN
CHALLENGES.
DID KIM TALK TO YOU TODAY?
NOT YET.
SHE ALREADY KNOWS THAT WE
KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
SABRINA.
OKAY.
D'UH.
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE.
SABRINA HAS NO IDEA HER ASS
IS ON THE LINE.
THAT'S WHY A BLIND SIDE IS SO
GREAT.
I AGREE.
IT'S AMAZING HOW WE CONTROL
THE SHOW.
THIS GAME IS OUR GAME.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE YESTERDAY I
WAS LIKE, SABRINA?
YOU'RE GOING HOME.
THEN TODAY AT THE CHALLENGE, I
MEAN, DID YOU SEE SABRINA?
SHE WAS THE FIRST ONE DONE.
I MEAN, I COULD BEAT HER.
SO THERE'S NO REASON WHY SABRINA
NEEDS TO GO.
BUT KAT, SHE JUST BROUGHT IT.
HOME GIRL WAS GIVING IT HER AL
AND, LIKE, THAT'S SOMEBODY THAT
I DO NOT WANT TO GO UP AGAINST
IF THAT'S HOW SHE'S GOING TO
PLAY THESE CHALLENGES.
PLEASE TELL ME WE'RE ON THE
SAME WAVELENGTH SO WE KEEP
SABRINA AND WE TAKE OUT KAT?
NO.
I WANT AN EASIER WIN.
I CAN'T KEEP GOING UP AGAINST
KAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I DON'T WANT IT TO GET LIKE A
TROY THING WHERE WE CAN'T GET
KAT OUT.
ALICIA CAME UP TO ME AND SHE
SAID "I DON'T KNOW HOW WE GOT
INTO THIS POSITION BUT KAT HAS
TO GO IMMEDIATELY."
I WAS TOTALLY SHOCKED.
I SAW SOME BIG LOGS RIGHT
THERE THERE.
I'M GOING TO GO IN A SECOND.
NICE.
HEY.
KAT.
THAT'S THE VOTE?
I MEAN DID YOU SEE HOW HARD
SHE WENT ON THAT CHALLENGE?
AS MUCH AS YOU THINK SHE
CAN'T WIN, SHE CAN.
I DO THINK KAT HAS A GOOD
SHOT AT GETTING A LOT OF JURY
VOTES BECAUSE SHE HASN'T PISSED
A LOT OF PEOPLE OFF.
BUT I THINK SABRINA'S A BIGGER
THREAT.
SHE'S SMART ENOUGH TO SWAY THE
JURY AND TOTALLY SCREW ME OVER
IN THE END.
LET'S JUST STOP TALKING.
THAT'S THE VOTE?
OKAY, GOOD.
I WOULD RATHER SEE SABRINA GO
FIRST BEFORE WE TAKE KAT OUT.
SO KAT'S GOING TO VOTE SABRINA
AND I THINK TARZAN WOULD BE
WILLING TO GET RID OF SABRINA.
SO IT KIND OF FEELS LIKE CHELSEA
AND I ARE THE SWING VOTES.
ALICIA CAME TO ME AND SHE'S
REALLY, REALLY WORRIED KAT IS
GOING TO WIN.
NOW SHE WANTS TO TAKE KAT OUT
NEXT.
OH, MY GOD!
YEAH.
SHE'S LIKE "SHE'S GONNA WIN."
I DON'T KNOW THAT IT BENEFITS
US.
I'LL START THINKING ABOUT
THAT AND THAT MAKES ME NERVOUS
BECAUSE SAB IS SO SMART.
ALL OF A SUDDEN ALICIA AN I
ARE ON THE SAME PAGE THAT KAT
NEEDS TO GO.
SHE'S SELFISH AND DOESN'T
DESERVE TO BE IN THE FINAL
THREE.
BUT KIM STILL WANTS TO VOTE OUT
SABRINA.
I UNDERSTAND WHERE SHE'S COMING
FROM, BUT I FEEL LIKE SABRINA'S
BEEN ON KIM AND I'S SIDE SINCE
DAY ONE.
SO YOU DON'T THINK THAT SINCE
SHE HAS HER MIND-SET ON KAT THAT
WE SHOULD TAKE HER OUT FIRST?
WELL, I WOULD SAY SHE
DOESN'T...
BEFORE SHE CHANGES HER MIND?
I'M JUST TRYING TO MAKE SURE
THAT'S WHAT WE WANT TO DO.
KIM AND I ARE GOING TO AGREE
100% ON WHAT WHATEVER WE DECIDE
TO DO BUT I THINK FROM HERE ON
OUT IT'S GOING TO BE A KAT
FIGHT.
ARE YOU GOOD FOR TONIGHT?
I'VE BEEN TOLD KAT.
I'M NOT SURE THAT THAT'S THE
CASE ANYMORE.
I STILL HAVE SOME CHOICES FOR
SURE TONIGHT BUT CHELSEA AND I
HAVE HAD AN ALLIANCE WITH
SABRINA SINCE DAY ONE AND KAT, I
THINK SHE LOOKS AT ME LIKE A BIG
SISTER SO THIS IS NOT A FUN VOTE
TONIGHT.
WELL, THAT'S PROBABLY SMART.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT BOSS LADY.
STOP!
THAT'S TRUE.
TO ME IT'S A GAME-CHANGING
DECISION.
I'M ABOUT TO MAKE A CHOICE AND
IT'S GOING TO BE A BLIND SIDE
EITHER WAY BUT THIS IS A GAME
AND THERE'S NO WAY TO KEEP
EVERYBODY HAPPY AT THIS POINT IN
THE GAME.
IT'S GOING TO GO TO HELL FROM
HERE ON OUT.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JONAS, MICHAEL, JAY, LEIF, AND
TROYZAN VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, KAT, WE GO FROM LAST WEEK
WHERE YOU'RE DEVASTATED BECAUSE
YOU DON'T GET PICKED TO GO ON
THE REWARD TO THIS WEEK WHERE
YOU NOW HAVE THE GOOD NEWS/BAD
NEWS SCENARIO OF GETTING TO PICK
TWO PEOPLE TO GO ALONG WITH YOU,
WHICH MEANS YOU'RE LEAVING THE
OTHER FOUR BEHIND.
IT WAS PROBABLY THE HARDEST
THING I'VE EVER HAD TO DO IN MY
LIFE.
WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING AT ALL OF
THESE BEAUTIFUL FACES WITH THEIR
FAMILIES AND YOU HAVE TO PICK
TWO PEOPLE.
IT'S VERY FRUSTRATING AND IT
DOES HURT MY FEELINGS.
Jeff: IT HURTS "YOUR"
FEELINGS?
YEAH, BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO
SEE THEIR FACES BE MAD.
Jeff: HERE'S WHAT I WANT TO
UNDERSTAND.
LAST REWARD CHALLENGE KIM DIDN'T
PICK YOU.
FIRST PERSON YOU PICK IS KIM.
YES.
STRATEGICALLY I COULD HAVE
PICKED TWO DIFFERENT PEOPLE BUT
AT THAT TIME I WAS THINKING MORE
LIKE WHO WOULD I HAVE A GREAT
TIME WITH NOT THINKING
STRATEGICALLY.
NOW, THAT'S MY OWN CHOICE.
Jeff: SABRINA, DO YOU BUY
THAT?
THAT KAT WAS NOT THINKING ABOUT
STRATEGY WHEN SHE PICKED TWO OF
THE PEOPLE WHO WENT ON THE LAST
REWARD?
I DON'T THINK STRATEGY HAD
ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
I THINK HONESTLY THE 22-YEAR-OLD
LIKE "I WANT TO HAVE FUN."
AND I THINK IT'S SOMETHING SHE'S
GOING TO LOOK BACK AT AND REGRET
BECAUSE MOST PEOPLE UP HERE
WOULD HAVE PICKED TARZAN AND
CHRISTINA SIMPLY BECAUSE OF
THEIR LOVED ONES BACK STORY.
BUT IT'S HER CHOICE.
Jeff: .
JEFF, AGAIN, I AM 22, I AM A
LITTLE NAIVE AND I'M SORRY THAT
I PICKED PEOPLE THAT OBVIOUSLY
EVERYONE ELSE DIDN'T AGREE WITH.
Jeff: CHELSEA, DO YOU BUY
THAT KAT IS 22 AND NAIVE OR IS
THAT A GREAT STRATEGY?
IT'S, LIKE, THAT'S HER WAY
OUT EVERY TIME SHE SCREWS UP.
EVERY TIME SOMEONE GETS ON HER
CASE ABOUT HOW SELFISH SHE IS
SHE SAYS "YEAH, I'M 22, GET OFF
MY BACK.
IT'S LIKE IT ALWAYS COMES DOWN
TO HER AGE AND 22 IS NOT THAT
YOUNG.
IS THIS WHOLE TRIBAL COUNCIL
ABOUT ME?
LIKE, I HAD NO IDEA THIS IS...
THIS WAS GOING TO HAPPEN.
Jeff: TARZAN, YOU'RE AN
OLDER MAN WHO'S HAD LIFE
EXPERIENCE.
WHERE DO YOU WEIGH IN ON THIS?
I KNOW SHE WANTED TO HAVE FUN
WITH THE GIRLS.
I'M AN OLD MAN.
SHE DIDN'T THINK ABOUT MY
CIRCUMSTANCE OR ABOUT MY WIFE.
SHE'S 22.
AND SO THINGS LIKE THIS DON'T
HIT HER YET BECAUSE SHE'S TOO
YOUNG TO HAVE EXPERIENCED ENOUGH
THINGS IN LIFE.
SO IT DIDN'T BOTHER ME AT ALL.
Jeff: ALICIA, LET'S TALK
ABOUT TODAY'S CHALLENGE FOR
IMMUNITY.
SABRINA'S FIRST OUT.
AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME IS
THAT GOOD NEWS THAT SHE'S OUT
EARLY AND NOT SEEN AS THE A
THREAT?
IS IT BAD NEWS BECAUSE YOU CAN'T
HANG IN THERE, MAN, YOU DON'T
DESERVE TO GO TO THE END.
I WAS SURPRISED SABRINA GOT
OUT FIRST.
MY VOTE WOULD HAVE BEEN FOR
TARZAN, YOU KNOW?
(LAUGHS)
I'M SORRY.
MAYBE IT'S HER GAME TO NOT SHOW
HERSELF AS A PHYSICAL THREAT.
Jeff: GO TO THE OTHER END.
KAT AND KIM DUKE IT OUT TO THE
END.
I EXPECT THAT FROM KIM, SHE
BRINGS IT.
CAT I WAS VERY SHOCKED.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT SHE HAD IT IN
HER.
Jeff: DOES KAT EARN RESPECT
FOR HANGING IN THE CHALLENGE
THAT LONG?
DEFINITELY.
HOWEVER I WAS A LITTLE BAFFLED
HOW SHE REACTED BECAUSE SHE WAS
SO UPSET WITH KIM.
Jeff: I WASN'T UPSET WITH
KIM, I WAS UPSET WITH MYSELF
THAT MY BAD I DO GAVE OUT.
KIM WENT TO GIVE YOU A HIGH
FIVE AND YOU KIND OF SNUFFED
HERE.
DUDE, WHAT IS THIS?
Jeff: SABRINA, WHAT'S THE
VIBE AROUND CAMP?
YOU PRETTY MUCH DECIMATED THE
GUYS.
NOW WE'RE GETTING DOWN TO IT.
IT'S GETTING A LITTLE TESTY.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY I
APPRECIATE HONESTY.
TO ME THAT'S WHEN PEOPLE GET
RESPECT.
Jeff: KIM, DO YOU THINK
BEING TOO HONEST IF YOU GET TO
THE END CAN BE AN ASSET AND
THEREFORE MAKE YOU A THREAT?
YEAH.
I MEAN, TO ME IT'S BAD NEWS.
I'VE SEEN PEOPLE WIN THIS GAME
THAT SHOOT STRAIGHT AND
EVERYBODY LOVES THEM AND IT'S
LIKE AN ENDEARING QUALITY IN
THIS GAME WHICH ALSO MAKES ME
NERVOUS.
Jeff: SABRINA, WORRIED AT
ALL THAT YOU MAY NOT GET TO THE
END BECAUSE PEOPLE THINK "SHE IS
TOO WELL SPOKEN AND SHE HASN'T
LIED?"
IT DEPENDS ON WHAT PEOPLE
VALUE.
LIKE, TO BE HONEST, I WILL GO
STRAIGHT UP MY EMOTIONS.
SO THE PERSON THAT MAY HAVE
PISSED ME OFF, THEY DON'T GET MY
VOTE AND THEY COULD BE THE BEST
PLAYER IN THIS GAME.
Jeff: SO, KAT, SABRINA VERY
BLACK-AND-WHITE IS SAYING
LISTEN, IF I END UP ON THE JURY,
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU RIGHT NOW
YOU MAY NOT LIKE HOW I VOTE
BECAUSE I MAY JUST BE IN A BAD
MOOD SO IF YOU BLIND SIDE ME,
HELLO, WATCH OUT.
UM, IF IT IS GOING TO BE A
BLIND SIDE, IT'S GOING TO BE
PRETTY FUNNY AND PRETTY, LIKE,
EXCITING.
Jeff: WHY WOULD BIT FUN AND
EXCITING?
I DON'T KNOW.
BECAUSE BLIND SIDES ARE ALWAYS
FUN AND EXCITING.
YOU'RE LIKE... YOU KNOW?
I ALWAYS GET EXCITED IF
SOMETHING LIKE THAT GOES DOWN
AND IF IT DOES, COOL BEANS.
IF IT DOESN'T, TOUCHE.
WHATEVER.
(LAUGHS)
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT'S TIME TO GET TO THE VOTE.
KIM HAS IMMUNITY.
YOU CAN NOT VOTE FOR KIM.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
TARZAN, YOU'RE UP.
SABRINA, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
BUT IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
KAT, YOU'RE A LITTLE BIT UNTAMED
TO TAKE TO THE TOP.
I'M SURE YOU'LL LEARN THIS LIFE
LESSON LATER ON.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SABRINA.
KAT.
ONE VOTE SABRINA; ONE VOTE KAT.
TWO VOTES KAT; ONE VOTE SABRINA.
KAT.
THAT'S THREE VOTES KAT; ONE VOTE
SABRINA.
Jeff: 12th PERSON VOTED
OUT AND THE SIXTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY, KAT, I HAVE TO ASK YOU TO
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
KAT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
(SOBBING)
Jeff: WELL, JUDGING FROM
KAT'S REACTION, THAT WAS A BIG
OLD BLIND SIDE AND THE MESSAGE
IS PRETTY SIMPLE: IF IT COULD
HAPPEN TO HER; IT CAN HAPPEN TO
YOU.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"... THE LAST MAN
STANDING IS LOSING IT.
A FAILURE AMONG MEN.
THIS ISN'T OFFENSIVE TO ANYBODY
HERE IF I WORE THIS, RIGHT?
Jeff: BUT THERE'S A METHOD
TO HIS MADNESS.
I THINK YOU GUYS HAVE A
BETTER CHANCE IF I'M ONE OF THE
THREE.
THE GIRLS THINK I'VE GIVEN UP
BUT I WANT TO WIN THE GAME.
I'M PROUD OF MYSELF BUT,
LIKE, I JUST DON'T BELIEVE IT
WAS MY TIME TO GO AND I LEFT
BEFORE CHRISTINA AND TARZAN!
LIKE, ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
(SOBBING)
I'M GOING TO GO DOWN AS THE MOST
NAIVE PERSON IN THE WHOLE GAME.
I'M GOING TO BEG JEFF TO LET ME
PLAY AGAIN SO I CAN REDEEM
MYSELF