Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": WITH THE WOMEN
PICKING OFF THE MEN ONE BY ONE,
IT SEEMED OBVIOUS THAT TARZAN
WOULD GO NEXT.
BUT AN EMOTIONAL VISIT FROM THE
CASTAWAYS' LOVED ONES SET A
DIFFERENT BALL IN MOTION.
GO!
IN AN INTENSE AWARD CHALLENGE--
WE'RE ALMOST THERE, DAD.
Jeff: KAT WON A TRIP AWAY
FROM CAMP WITH HER LOVED ONE.
KAT'S DECISION NOT TO TAKE
TARZAN
AND HIS WIFE OF 30 YEARS AND
CHRISTINA AND HER ALING FATHER
DID NOT SIT WELL WITH SABRINA.
BACK AT CAMP, SABRINA VENTED
ABOUT KAT'S SELFISHNESS.
THIS IS DEFINITELY ENOUGH
REASON TO MAKE ME VOTE OFF KAT.
Jeff: IN A GRUELING
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE-- YOU ARE
HAVING TO EARN IT RIGHT HERE--
KAT FOUGHT TO THE BITTER END,
BUT IT WAS KIM HOPREVAILED.
KIM WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
AFTER THE CHALLENGE, ALICIA
JOINED THE SWELLING TIDE TO TAKE
OUT KAT.
KIM, WANTING TO KEEP HER OPTIONS
OPEN, WASN'T SO SURE.
I DO THINK KAT HAS A GOOD
SHOT AT GETTING A LOT OF JURY
VOTES JUST BECAUSE SHE HASN'T
PISSED A LOT OF PEOPLE OFF BUT I
THINK SABRINA IS SMART ENOUGH TO
SWAY THE JURY AND TOTALLY SCREW
ME OVER IN THE END.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
KAT FELT VERY CONFIDENT.
IF IT IS GOING TO BE A
BLINDSIDE, IT'S GOING TO BE
PRETTY FUNNY AND PRETTY, LIKE--
LIKE, EXCITING.
Jeff: BUT KIM HAD TO
DECIDE.
DEVASTATING KAT, AND SHAKING UP
THE GAME.
KAT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
WILL THE WOMEN CONTINUE TO TAKE
OUT THEIR OWN?
OR WILL TARZAN, THE LAST MAN
STANDING, BE THE NEXT TO GO?
SIX ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT?
MAN.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT DAMAGE
CONTROL.
HER LAST STATEMENT WAS HOW
FUNNY A BLINDSIDE IS.
OH, MY GOD!
HOW IRONIC WAS THAT?
FIWERE-- IF I WERE THE GIRLS,
I WOULD HAVE VOTED MEET OUT
BEFORE KAT.
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN THE
SMARTEST THING THEY COULD DO BUT
THEY DIDN'T DO IT.
AND NOW THAT THEY'VE DONE THAT,
I HAVE A SUBPLOT WHERE I MIGHT
BE ABLE TO ARRANGE MYSELF TO BE
THE TOP THREE.
BUT OF COURSE I WOULDN'T REVEAL
ANY OF THAT RIGHT NOW.
I'M JUST HOPING TO MAKE IT TO
FOUR.
YOU'RE NOT OPPOSED TO ME GETTING
DOWN TO NUMBER FOUR, RIGHT?
NOT AT ALL.
OKAY, SO I'M THINKING THE
BEST THING FOR YOU LADIES WOULD
BE FOR YOU, ALICIA, AND
CHRISTINA TO BE THE LAST THREE
STANDING, BECAUSE NOBODY WILL
VOTE FOR CHRISTINA.
I KNOW.
AND IF I GO ON THE JURY, I
THINK I CAN CONVINCE THEM TO
VOTE FOR YOU.
HERE'S MY ONLY CONCERN.
YEAH.
IS I JUST START TO WONDER IF
ALICIA IS REALLY GOING TO WANT
TO TAKE ME.
OKAY, WELL, I THINK ALICIA
HAS A STRONG AFFINITY FOR YOU AS
FAR AS JUST LIKING YOU AND
WANTING TO BE YOUR FRIEND AND,
YOU KNOW, GO WITH WHATEVER YOU
SAY.
BUT HERE'S THE THING, THE
BIGGEST THREAT IS--
CHELSEA.
AND SHE'S MY FRIEND.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S SO HARD.
WHEN WE GOT BACK FROM TRIBAL
TONIGHT TARZAN PULLED ME ASIDE
AND WANTED TO TELL ME WHAT HE
THOUGHT THE BEST PLAN FOR ME WAS
AND THAT IS I GET RID OF CHELSEA
AND ALICIA, AND AS CRAZY AS
TARZAN IS, IT IS WHAT I KNOW TO
BE TRUE.
IF I SEND CHELSEA HOME, THAT
WILL BE MY WORST NIGHT HERE.
YOU ALL STAY AND I'LL GO.
OKAY.
WHEN YOU--
WAIT, DO YOU THINK-- MY THING
IS I KNOW I CAN BEAT CHRISTINA,
BUT DO YOU THINK I CAN WIN
AGAINST-- KIM, KIM IS MY WHOLE--
MY PLAN IS TO HYPE IT UP FOR
YOU WHEN I GET ON THE JURY.
SEE, AND I DON'T THINK IT WILL
BE HARD TO DO AT ALL.
BECAUSE THEY FEEL BETRAYED BY
HER.
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS IN
SEGMENTS.
DON'T BE THE FIRST ONE VOTE OUT.
MAKE IT TO THE MERGE, MAKE IT TO
SEEING MY WIFE.
MAKING IT TO NUMBER FOUR.
AND MAYBE SLIPPING INTO NUMBER
THREE.
EVEN IF I MAKE IT TO THREE, AND
I LOSE, IT WON'T BE A TERRIBLE
THING.
I JUST WON'T BUY SHOCKS FOR MY
CAR.
THAT'S ALL.
LOOK, THIS IS A CUP.
LOOK HOW MUCH IS INSIDE OF IT.
IT MIGHT JUST BE BETTER TO
SAVE IT FOR DINNER.
RIGHT NOW, I FEEL LIKE THE
GAME IS THREE VERSUS THREE.
SABRINA, KIM, AND I, AND ALICIA,
CHRISTINA AND TARZAN.
I GENUINELY THINK THAT ALICIA,
CHRISTINA AND TARZAN THINK THEY
HAVE KIM IN THEIR ALLIANCE,
WHICH IS GREAT, BECAUSE I KNOW
THAT SHE'S GOT MY BACK.
DUE, I'VE BEEN DREAMING ABOUT
FOOD ALL NIGHT, AND I WAS JUST
LIKE WHY DO I KEEP ON DREAMING
ABOUT FOOD?
TODAY'S REWARD, I SOMEHOW
PULL OUT A WINNER, THEN I THINK
YOU NEED TO GO.
YOU'RE SO SWEET.
I FEEL THE SAME.
I'M TRYING TO REEL CHRISTINA
IN A LITTLE BIT.
I KNOW THAT CHRISTINA IS
ALICIA'S PUPPET, AND I'M TRYING
TO HELP HER SEE THE BIG SCHEME
OF THINGS, THE BIG PICTURE.
I THINK ALICIA WANTS TO TAKE YOU
AND TARZAN.
BUT I THINK JUST BECAUSE HE'S A
MALE AND ALL THOSE GUYS ARE
PISSED AT THE GIRLS, THAT
THEY'RE GONNA VOTE FOR HIM, AND
THAT MEANS HE CAN'T GO TO THE
END.
IF I CAN GET CHRISTINA TO SEE
THAT TARZAN CAN'T GO TO THE
FINAL THREE, MAYBE SHE'LL FALL
IN WITH KIM AND I.
I FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE SOME KIND
OF BOND WITH ALICIA.
SO IF YOU COULD KEEP THAT
BETWEEN US BECAUSE I'M JUST
TALKING OUT LOUD RIGHT NOW.
BUT--
YEAH, I'LL JUST KEEP IT QU
QUIET.
SHUT UP.
NO KIDDING, NO JOKE.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
IF THERE WAS AN AWARD
CHALLENGE AND SHE COULD TAKE TWO
SHE SAID,"I'M GOING TO TAKE
YOU."
AND THEN SHE SAID ME, AND ALICIA
AND TARZAN ARE IN ALLIANCE FOR
THE FINAL THREE.
WHEN CHELSEA AND CHRISTINA
WENT TO TREE MAIL, CHRISTINA
TOLD US EVERYTHING CHELSEA SAID
ON THEIR WALK.
MY FIRST QUESTION I WANTED
ANSWER WAS DID CHELSEA BLOW MY
COVER BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN
PLAYING BOTH SIDES?
ALICIA, TARZAN, AND CHRISTINA
ALL THINK I MAKE A FOUR SOME
FOR THEM, AND THEN CHELSEA AND
SABRINA THINK I AM THEIR THIRD.
SHUT UP.
I'M TELLING YOU, IT'S THEM
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S THEM AGAINST US.
GOD, THAT MAKES ME WANT TO
KICK CHRISTINA'S ASS.
DON'T SAY A WORD.
I WON'T.
IT WILL RUIN IT.
SETTING YOURSELF UP IN A
POSITION TO PLAY BOTH SIDES IS
BRILLIANT BUT IT'S ALSO ONE OF
THE SCARIER PLACES TO SIT IN
THIS GAME BECAUSE IT JUST TAKES
ONE CONVERSATION BETWEEN TWO
PEOPLE ON OPPOSITE SIDES TO PUT
IT ALL TOGETHER AND THEN YOU'RE
THE FIRST PERSON GONE BECAUSE
NOBODY TRUSTS YOU ANYMORE.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU ARE GOING TO RACE
TO RELEASE A DISK BY SPINNING
AROUND IT.
THIS WILL MAKE YOU DIZZY.
YOU'LL TAKE THE DISK, MOVE TO
THE NEXT STATION, WHERE YOU WILL
DO IT AGAIN.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL THREE
DISKS, YOU WILL USE THEM TO FORM
A DECODER.
YOU'LL USE THE DECODER TO GIVE
YOU THE THREE NUMBERS YOU NEED
TO SOLVE THE COMBINATION BOX.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT AND
RAISE THEIR FLAG WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
YES.
Jeff: THE WINNER OF TODAY'S
CHALLENGE WILL LEAVE HERE AND BE
TAKEN TO A YACHT.
YOU'LL GO OUT ON THE OCEAN,
COCKTAILS, TAKE A SHOWER.
SHOWER!
Jeff: WE'LL GIVE YOU FRESH
CLOTHES.
AND THEN YOU'LL HAVE A NICE
THREE-COURSE MEAL AT SUNSET AND
SLEEP ON THE BOAT, RETURNING TO
CAMP IN THE MORNING.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
YES!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'LL DRAW
FOR SPOTS AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO, FOR AN AFTERNOON ON
A YACHT.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
SPIN AROUND THOSE DISKS.
KIM, FLYING AROUND HERS.
SABRINA HAS HERS FREE.
KIM IS FREE.
KIM'S DITZY.
ALICIA'S FREE.
THIS WILL MAKE YOU DIZZY.
OH, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
Jeff: CHRISTINA VERY DIZZY.
SABRINA ONCE AGAIN IS FIRST OUT.
CHELSEA HAS HER SECOND DISK.
ALICIA VERY DIZZY AS SHE MOVES
FROM HER SECOND TO HER THIRD
DISK.
TARZAN HAS HIS SECOND DISK!
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR LASK
DISK.
34 DAYS OF VERY LITTLE FOOD AND
EVERYBODY'S LIGHTHEADED, BUT
EVERYBODY WANTS THIS REWARD.
SABRINA AND KIM ARE FIRST TO THE
DECODER.
ALICIA NOW AT THE DECODER.
CHELSEA HAS HER LAST DISK.
TARZAN NOW WORKING ON THE
DECODER.
EVERYBODY TRYING TO SOLVE THE
DECODER, LOOKING FOR THREE
NUMBERS THAT WILL OPEN UP THAT
COMBINATION BOX.
YOU'VE GOT TO SPIN THESE PIECES
UNTIL THE NUMBERS LINE UP.
IF YOU THINK YOU HAVE THREE,
GIVE IT A TRY.
CHELSEA THINKS SHE HAS IT, AND
SHE'S GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
IT IS NOT RIGHT.
YOU MAY HAVE THE RIGHT THREE
NUMBERS.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THEM IN THE
RIGHT ORDER ON THAT COMBINATION
BOX.
ALICIA NOW HAS HER'S SOLVED.
SHE'S TRYING TO FIGURE IT OUT.
IT'S ALICIA AND CHELSEA.
CHELSEA CHANGING THE NUMBERS
ONCE AGAIN.
WILL THIS BE RIGHT?
NO.
GOTTA TRY AGAIN.
ALICIA GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
SHE'S WRONG.
CHELSEA STILL WORKING THOSE
NUMBERS.
SO MANY DIFFERENT COMBINATIONS.
KIM NOW GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
CHRISTINA HAS SOLVED HER
DECODER.
CHELSEA PULLS IT OUT.
AND WINS REWARD.
YES, YES, YES!
OH, MY GOD!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
Jeff: CHELSEA, COME ON
OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
NICE JOB.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE
HERE, BE TAKEN TO A NICE YACHT,
TAKE A SHOWER, GET SOME FRESH
CLOTHES.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: THEN YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE A NICE DINNER AT SUNSET AND
A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP AND YOU
CANNOT DO THIS ALONE SO YOU'RE
GOING TO CHOOSE SOMEBODY TO COME
WITH YOU.
I JUST KNOW KAT CAUGHT A LOT
OF GRIEF FOR WHO SHE CHOSE IN
THE LAST REWARD SO I'M GOING TO
PLAY IT FAIR, LIKE I'VE PLAYED
THIS HOLE GAME, AND I THINK
SABRINA NEEDS TO GO WITH ME
BECAUSE SHE HASN'T HAD MUCH FOOD
AND I KNOW SHE'S AS EXHAUSTED AS
I AM.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LOVE YOU, GIRL.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CHELSEA.
ONE MORE PERSON IS COMING WITH
YOU.
I WANT KIM TO GO.
Jeff: KIM, COME ON OVER.
LOVE YOU.
Jeff: THE THREE OF YOU ARE
GOING TO HAVE A WONDERFUL
AFTERNOON.
ALICIA, TARZAN, CHRISTINA, GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GUYS, GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD OUT.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
Jeff: NICE WORK.
LADIES, YOUR CABIN.
COOL!
OKAY, THIS IS YOUR CABIN.
YOUR CLEAN CLOTHES.
I'VE NEVER ONCE BEEN ON A
SAILBOAT.
NOT ONLY A SAILBOUT BUT THIS HAS
TO BE ONE OF THE NICEST
SAILBOATS EVER.
YOU SHOWER FIRST.
REALLY?
YES.
IT'S GOT A FULL KITCHEN, A
BEDROOM, A SHOWER.
I MEAN, IT'S THE WORKS.
OH, MY GOSH!
I WAS IN THE SHOWER FOR PROBABLY
30 MINUTES.
I MEAN I SCRUBBED, AND JUST
KNOWING THAT I'M CLEAN NOW MAKES
A WORLD OF DIFFERENCE.
ALL RIGHT, CHEERS, TO THE END.
ALL THE WAY.
OH, MY GOD.
CHELSEA, DARLING.
OH, YOU LOOK SO AMAZING.
I'M A NEW WOMAN.
HERE'S YOUR CENTER SEAT.
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY!
WHENEVER YOU STEP OUT OF THE
GAME AND YOU GET TO GO ON THESE
REWARDS, IT'S LIKE YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE HUMAN AGAIN.
I'LL SEE YOU, LADIES.
I MEAN, I KIND OF KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON BACK AT CAMP, SO SINCE
I DO, I CAN COME OUT HERE AND
RELAX AND THE THREE OF US WILL
TRY TO WORK IT OUT AND MAKE TO
THE END TOGETHER.
WOW, I LOVE CHAMPAGNE.
DO YOU LOVE THAT?
I LOVE YOU.
YES, THIS IS REAL GOOD.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
OH, MY GOD.
THE THING IS I THINK WE CAN DO
IT.
THAT'S WHAT I GET EXCITED ABOUT.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE ON A
HONEYMOON RIGHT NOW.
WE ARE.
YOU START TO FEEL LIKE AN ANIMAL
OUT HERE.
YOU GET REAL SAVAGE SO TO JUST
GO AND BE WAITED ON AND TO FEEL
SO PAMPERED, I STARTED TO
REMEMBER WHOIS AND WHAT I'M
ABOUT AND WHAT I'M DOING HERE.
I FEEL LIKE MY HEAD IS SO MUCH
CLEARER TODAY THAN IT WAS
YESTERDAY SO THE REWARD WAS HUGE
FOR ME.
I'M-- I'M LIVID.
OH, YOU'RE LIVID.
SO AM I.
SO, CHELSEA WAS ASKED, "WHO
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO ON THE
REWARD WITH?"
AND HER RESPONSE S, I'M GOING TO
PICK THE PERSON HOW I PLAY THE
GAME, WHICH IS FAIR."
SO WHO DOES SHE PICK?
KIM.
WHY THE HELL DOES KIM NEED TO GO
ON A THIRD REWARD.
TELL ME TO MY FACE, THAT WAS A
FAIR CHOICE.
NO, AND NOT ONLY THAT, ON THE
WALK FROM TREE MAIL--
SHE SAID SHE WOULD TAKE YOU.
THAT'S WHY IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
US THREE DON'T BUDGE ON WHO WE
VOTE NEXT.
WHO ARE WE VOTING FOR?
WE'RE VOTING FOR CHELSEA.
THAT MEANS OUR THREE VOTES
NEED TO BE ALIGNED.
THEIR THREE VOTES ARE GOING TO
BE A TIE.
THAT MEANS WE HAVE TO FORCE ONE
OF THEM, WHICH WOULD BE KIM, TO
STICK TRUE TO WHAT SHE SAID.
KIM AND I TRUST EACH OTHER BUT
I'M NOT GOING TO PASS IT BY HER
THAT SHE'S NOT THINKING OF, YOU
KNOW, OTHER THINGS, OTHER
OPTIONS.
HOWEVER I THINK IT IS STUPID
THAT SHE WOULD WANT TO SIT NEXT
TO SABRINA AND CHELSEA.
TARZAN, MYSELF AND CHRISTINA ARE
SOLID AND IF THEY WANT TO BE
SOLID, COOL, LET THEM BE SOILED.
LET THEM DRAW ROCKS.
LET THEM BE STUPID.
WHEN THEY COME BACK, IF KIM
COMES BACK AND SAYS LET'S NOT DO
CHELSEA, LET'S DO, BLAH, BLAH,
BLAH, THAT WOULD BE A DEAD GIVE
AWAY.
THE TWO BIG PLAYERS WHO WILL
KNOCK YOU GUYS OUT OF THE LAST
THREE ARE KIM AND CHELSEA AND I
BELIEVE THEY'RE DECEIVING US AND
THAT THEY'RE A TEAM.
SO I THINK YOU GUYS HAVE A
BETTER CHANCE IF I'M ONE OF THE
THREE ACTUALLY BECAUSE THOSE
THREE LADIES TOOK OFF.
IT'S SORT OF ALMOST A BLESSING
IN DISGUISE BECAUSE IT HELPED
UNITE ANOTHER PLOT THAT MIGHT
ALLOW ME TO SAY HERE POSSIBLY TO
THE LAST THREE.
SO--
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
WOULD YOU RATHER SIT NEXT TO HIM
OR WOULD YOU RATHER SIT NEXT TO
KIM?
I'M GOING TO BE PERFECTLY
HONEST, I THINK KIM IS PROBABLY
GOING TO GET MORE VOTES VERSUS
TARZAN.
IT'S NOT MUCH OF A THREAT.
ALL RIGHT, SO THIS IS THE
NEXT MOVE.
CHELSEA OR KIM.
I'M ACTUALLY LEANING TOWARDS
TAKING TARZAN TO THE TOP THREE
WITH CHRISTINA AND I.
SO KIM BETTER COME BACK WITH THE
RIGHT STORY THAT WE'RE STILL
STICKING TO CHELSEA, AND WHO
KNOWS?
AFTER CHELSEA'S GONE, YOU KNOW
WHAT?
TARZAN HAS A GREAT POINT-- WE
NEED TO TAKE HIM OUT.
I LOVE ME SOME GRILLED
VEGGIE.
WOW!
OH, MY GOD, IF I WAS BACK AT
CAMP RIGHT NOW, I'D BE A MESS.
I'D BE SOMEWHERE BALLED UP
CRYING.
I'D BE TRYING TO DROWN.
THIS IS WHAT-- THIS IS THE
DETERMINING FACTOR.
IT'S EITHER GOING TO BE US OR
IT'S GOING TO BE THEM.
GOTCHA.
AS LONG AS THEIR VOTES ARE
SPLIT, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK THEY'RE EVEN
QUESTIONING ME.
I DON'T THINK THEY EVER HAVE.
SOMEBODY HAS TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE.
KIM HAS AN AMAZING ABILITY TO
LOOK AT YOU, ALMOST LOOK THROUGH
YOU AND SAY, "YEAH, I'M WITH
YOU," AND IT'S BELIEVABLE.
YOU HAVE SUCH A PURE EFFECT ON
THEM.
YOU JUST LOOK AT THEM AND THE
BIG BABY BLUES.
I'M SCAERG MYSELF.
I CAN'T TELL WHEN I'M TELLING
THE TRUTH OR NOT.
THE REWARD, I THINK IT CLEARED
THE LINE FOR ME A LITTLE BIT.
I FEEL BETTER ABOUT THE OPTION
OF GOING WITH CHELSEA AND
SABRINA THAN JUST TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT ANY WAY POSSIBLE THAT
WE CAN SOMEHOW WIN THIS NEXT
VOTE WITH THREE VOTES.
WE GOTTA WIN TOMORROW.
MY PLANS FOR THE DAY, THE
FIRST THING I'M GOING TO DO IS
FIX ME SOME COCONUT STEW, START
THE FIRE, CLEAN MY CLOTHES, WASH
MY HAIR AGAIN.
I PREPARE TO BE DEFEATED IN SOME
KIND OF CONTEST LATER TODAY.
DEFEATED BY THE FEMININE GENDER.
FAILURE AMONG MEN.
I CAN DWRAIT MORE OF THIS.
NO, I'M GOING TO COOK IT THIS
MORNING THE WAY I WANT TO, OKAY.
SO DON'T BOTHER ME ABOUT IT.
AND WHAT WAY ARE YOU COOKING
IT?
THE WAY YOU WANT TO.
BUT, NO, HOW ARE YOU
PREPARING IT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
SO, SO.
SAME BUGS THAT WERE ON YOUR
SKIN.
I'M SURE CHRISTINA WOULD BE
MORE THAN WILLING TO LET YOU USE
HERS.
DON'T TOUCH MY BUFF!
I'M CLEANING MY BUFF RIGHT NOW.
I'VE HAD TO ENTER BATTLES
WITH MY BARE HANDS.
WHEN WE WENT OFF, YOU KNOW,
ON THE REWARD CHALLENGE WE GOT
STUFF AWAY FROM THE GAME, ALL
THE ARGUING, AND COMING BACK
HERE, THE SECOND WE WALK INTO
CAMP, THERE'S AN ARGUMENT, AND
IT'S JUST LIKE OH, WE'RE BACK IN
IT AGAIN.
TARZAN WAS LIKE IF KIM COMES
BACK SAYING A DIFFERENT TUNE,
SINGING A DIFFERENT TUNE GO BWHO
WE SHOULD VOTE, WE KNOW HE'S A
TRAITOR.
HE'S TRYING TO GET YOU ALL TO
TAKE HIM INSTEAD OF ME NOW.
SEE, THIS IS INTERESTING.
I DON'T KNOW, I JUST--
MAYBE THIS WAS HIS PLAN TO
PLAY STUPID.
I KNOW, I START TO--
TO PLAY STUPID--
IF HE ENDS UP WINNING THIS
THING I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING
WORSE, IT'S LIKE THE MEN WIN IN
THE END.
THE THOUGHT OF THAT MAKES ME
CRINGE.
I THINK THE ONLY REASON ARB
LASCH WOULD BE WILLING TO GIVE
UP TARZAN WHO HAS APPEARED TO BE
ONE OF HER MINIONS IS SHE'S
CONVINCED HE IS NOT A MINION
AFTER ALL THAT HE'S THE
MASTERMIND WHO WAS GOING TO TAKE
OUT HER MASTERMIND AND SHE WAS
GOING TO LOOK LIKE A FOOL.
IT'S ( BLEEP ).
HE'S PLAYING US.
YEAH.
HE'S GOING TO TAKE CHRISTINA!
AND SABRINA.
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY--
HE DOESN'T WANT TO TAKE US.
YES, YES, HE'S GOING TO
TAKE-- YOU KNOW WHY-- NO, NO,
HOW ABOUT THIS--
I JUST REALIZED I ALMOST GOT
MY ASS KICKED BY TARZAN.
WHEN KIM CAME BACK TODAY I
HAD TO CONFIDE IN HER AND WE
CROSS-REFERENCED EACH OTHER'S
STORIES AND WE ARE GETTING FED
THE SAME B.S..
HE'S GOING TO TAKE YOU.
I KNOW, WAIT.
TARZAN WANTS TO TAKE KIM OUT,
AND THEN SECURE HIS SPOT WITH
CHRISTINA AND SABRINA AND TAKE
ME OUT AND MAKE ME LOOK LIKE THE
FOOL.
HELL, NO!
HELL TO THE NO.
WE'RE GETTING PLAYED.
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
WE'RE SAVING OUR BUTTS.
HERE.
OKAY, OKAY.
WHAT DID HE TELL YOU--
HE COMES TO ME AND HE'S LIKE
CHRISTINA.
AND I SAID, WHAT?
HE SAYS ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
ALICIA?
AND I'M.
OH, MY GOD!
IF DIDN'T REALIZE THIS, I
WOULD HAVE GONE STRAIGHT UP
TARZAN.
I WOULD LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT IN
FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
NOW YOU'RE GETTING ALL PARANOID?
NOW YOU'RE TRYING TO PLAY THE
GAME?
NOW YOU'RE TRYING TO WORK THE
SOCIAL GAME?
I AM THE QUEEN OF THE SOCIAL
GAME.
IF CHELSEA WINS IMMUNITY, WE'RE
TAKING TARZAN OUT.
IF CHELSEA DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY,
THEN CHELSEA GOES HOME.
AND I DON'T FEEL BAD ABOUT THAT
CHOICE, EITHER, BECAUSE HOME
GIRL HAS BEEN TRYING TO RUN HER
GAME ON ME.
NO ONE RUNS HER GAME ON ME.
THAT'S THE GHETTO PUERTO RICAN
COMING OUT.
OH, WELL, I DON'T CARE.
DON'T TRY IT MAKE ME LOOK LIKE A
FOOL BY TRYING TO TAKE ME OUT AT
THE END.
I'M THE MOST POWERFUL PLAYER AND
I'M GOING TO REMAIN THE MOST
POWERFUL PLAYER.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE, KIM.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
USE THE LARGE FISH THOOKS PICK
UP BAGS OF PUZZLE PIECES.
YOU'LL THEN USE THE PIECES TO
COMPLETE A PUZZLE IN THE SHAPE
OF A FISH SKELETON.
TO MAKE IT A LITTLE MORE
INTERESTING, YOU'LL DO IT WITH
ONE HAND TIED BEHIND YOUR BACK.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
WINS IMMUNITY, GUARANTEE A ONE
IN FIVE SHOT AT WINNING THIS
GAME.
LOSERS, YOU WILL GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THE GAME.
LET'S DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU HAVE TO HOOK THREE
FISH HOOKS.
THEN YOU HAVE TO HOOK YOUR
PUZZLE PIECES WITH THE HOOKS.
KIM HAS HERS VERY QUICKLY.
ALICIA HAS HERS.
SABRINA HAS HERS.
TARZAN HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
CHRISTINA HAS IT.
NOW CHELSEA HAS IT.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR FIRST
BAG.
YOU'RE COMPLETING THE LOWEST
SECTION OF THE FISH SKELETON.
KIM OFF TO A QUICK START IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
ALICIA NOW GETTING IN ON IT.
CHELSEA NOW WORKING ON HER
PIECES.
EVERYBODY IN IT AT THIS POINT.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL OF THE BOTTOM
SECTION COMPLETED, YOU CAN HEAD
BACK AND GET THE NEXT BAG OF
PUZZLE PIECES.
KIM HAS HER LAST PIECE.
SHE'S HEADING BACK AND RIGHT ON
HER TAIL IS ALICIA.
CHELSEA HAS HER FIRST SECTION
COMPLETED.
CHELSEA, ALICIA, AND KIM NOW
WORKING ON THAT SECOND BAG OF
PUZZLE PIECES.
ALICIA NOW IN THE LEAD.
CHRISTINA FINISHES HER FIRST
SECTION.
KIM NOW HAS HER SECOND BAG.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
IT IS KIM AND ALICIA NOW WITH
THEIR SECOND BAGS OF PUZZLE
PIECES.
TARZAN FINALLY FINISHES HIS
FIRST SECTION.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
KIM GETS HER BAG UNDONE FASTER
THAN ALICIA.
KIM IS NOW BACK IN THE LEAD.
TARZAN NOW WORKING ON THAT
SECOND BAG, AND HE HAS IT.
TARZAN MAKES QUICK WORK OF THE
HOOKS.
THAT DEXTERITY IN THE HANDS OF A
SURGEON PAYING OFF.
CHRISTINA HAS HERS.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
BUT KIM AND ALICIA HAVE HAD A
BIG HEAD START IN THIS SECOND
STAGE.
SABRINA NOW BACK.
CHELSEA THE LAST ONE.
KIM FINISHES HER SECOND SECTION.
HEADING BACK FOR HER THIRD AND
FINAL BAG OF PUZZLE PIECES.
CHELSEA FINALLY GRABS ALL FOUR
RINGS.
CHELSEA HAS A LOT OF TIME TO
MAKE UP.
ALICIA FINISHES HER SECOND
SECTION.
ALICIA NOW WORKING ON THAT THIRD
AND FINAL SET OF HOOKS.
KIM STRUGGLING WITH THAT FIFTH
HOOK.
GIVING EVERYBODY ELSE A LOT OF
TIME TO CATCH UP.
TARZAN FINISHES HIS SECOND
SECTION.
TARZAN IS NOW IN THIS.
SABRINA AND CHRISTINA BOTH
FINISH THEIR SECOND SECTIONS.
EVERYBODY BUT CHELSEA NOW TRYING
TO GET THAT THIRD BAG OF PUZZLE
PIECES.
KIM HAD A HUGE LEAD.
AND SHE BLEW IT.
COULD NOT GET IT DONE.
AND ALICIA IS NOW BACK IN THE
LEAD.
SHE HAS HER THIRD BAG HEADING
BACK TO WORK ON IT.
BIG IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
GUARANTEED SPOT IN THE FINAL
FIVE.
CHELSEA FINISHES HER SECOND
SECTION.
SABRINA HAS HER FIVE HOOKS.
SHE'S WORKING ON THE THIRD
SECTION.
KIM WHO WAS IN THE LEAD FINALLY
HOOKS HER THIRD BAG AND CAN HEAD
BACK.
CHELSEA HAS HER THIRD BAG.
SHE'S NOW IN IT.
AND SHE DROPS IT JUST BEFORE
GETTING TO THE END.
THIS IS IT.
RIGHT HERE.
KIM, HUSTLING NOW, TROOIG TO
CATCH UP.
IT IS KIM AND ALICIA.
ALICIA IN THE LEAD.
KIM RIGHT BEHIND HER.
ALICIA VERY CLOSE NOW.
KIM PICKING UP THE PACE.
CLOSING THE GAP.
ALICIA HAS ONE PIECE LEFT AND
ONE DROPS.
ALICIA DROPS ANOTHER PIECE.
STARTING TO PANIC.
KIM WITH TWO PIECES LEFT.
ALICIA WITH TWO PIECES LEFT.
GOING TO COME DOWN TO THE WIRE.
KIM DROPS ONE!
GOTTA PICK UP ANOTHER.
ALICIA HAS IT.
ALICIA WINS IMMUNITY!
BY SECONDS OVER KIM.
ALICIA, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
IT WAS NECK AND NECK BETWEEN YOU
AND KIM.
YOU SNATCHED VICTORY AT THE LAST
SECOND.
YOUR FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
WIN.
AND IT MEANS ARE YOU SAFE
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND
YOU WILL BE IN THE FINAL FIVE.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, IT HAS
BEEN 36 VERY TOUGH DAYS, TOUGH
GAME TO PLAY.
CHELSEA, TARZAN, CHRISTINA, KIM,
SABRINA, FOR ONE OF YOU, IT WILL
COME TO AN END TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
I AM PROBABLY THE MOST
SURPRISED ABOUT MY WIN TODAY.
IT'S AWESOME.
IF I WAS BACK AT HOME I WOULD BE
WITH MY GIRLS SAYING, "LOOK AT
ME NOW."
YOU BE.
GREAT JOB, GIRL.
I SHOULD HAVE WON THAT.
YOU BITCH!
WHAT DID YOU CALL HER?
BITCH.
HOW DARE YOU BEAT ME?
ACTUALLY, I SHOULD HAVE WON
THAT.
THAT WASN'T EVEN ATHLETIC.
THANKS.
NO, I'M JUST SAYING, I SHOULD
HAVE.
TODAY IS ALL ABOUT ME.
AND I HAVE THE CHOICE, YOU KNOW,
KEEPING CHELSEA AROUND OR
TARZAN.
AND DO I GET RID OF MY POWER?
I CONTROL THREE VOTES-- MY VOTE,
TARZAN'S VOTE, AND CHRISTINA'S
VOTE.
BUT AS FAR AS TARZAN-- AND I
KIND VERY FAR THIS SELFISH VIBE,
LIKE SHOULD SHOULD I GIVE UP
POWER NOW?
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I'M AFRAID
HE'S GOING TO BACKSTAB ME.
BEFORE WE LEFT CAMP, I
CONVINCED ALICIA AND CHRISTINA
THAT TARZAN IS TRYING TO TAKE
YOU AND CHRISTINA-- SHUT UP.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
LIKE, LISTEN.
HE'S TRYING TO TAKE ME OUT.
SO I CONVINCED ALICIA IT'S ME
AND HER HE'S TRYING TO TAKE OUT
BECAUSE WE'RE THE TWO STRONGEST
PLAYER.
WE WENT THROUGH ALL THIS STUFF
ABOUT HOW INCONSISTENT HE'S
BEEN, WHAT HE SAID TO ALICIA.
THEY'RE FLOORED.
OH, MY GOD.
THEY'RE AS EXCITED TO TAKE
HIM OUT AS THEY WERE TO TAKE KAT
OUT.
WHAT.
I SWEAR.
SOMEHOW OR ANOTHER, KIM HAS
FINAGLED HER WAY INTO ALICIA'S
MINDSET THAT TARZAN IS GUNNING
FOR ALICIA.
NOW BEFORE, ALICIA, SHE WAS
GUNNING FOR CHELSEA FIRST.
BUT WHAT I JUST HEARD FROM KIM,
IF IT'S TRUE, WE CAN GET THIS
SUCKER TARZAN OUT OF HERE.
BUT ALICIA'S SLICK.
WE DON'T KNOW IF SHE'S TELLING
THE TRUTH.
SO WHO KNOWS?
SO SHE'S FREAKING OUT.
SHE THINKS HE'S COMING AFTER
HER, AND HE'S TRYING TO TAKE
SABRINA AND CHRISTINA.
THEY STILL WANT TO TAKE YOU OUT
FIRST THEN HIM.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO FROM
HERE.
I JUST KNOW THIS REALLY HELPS.
AND I-- I TRIED, LIKE, SO HARD,
I PUSHED FOR IT AS MUCH AS I
FELT I COULD PUSH FOR IT WITHOUT
MAKING IT REALLY OBVIOUS.
YEAH, YEAH.
BUT THEN I START TO GET
NERVOUS BECAUSE I'M, LIKE, WHAT
IF THEY'RE PLAYING ME?
AND THEY DO VOTE ME BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT HE'S GOING TO BE
SAYING.
AND I COULD GO HOME.
NOT IF YOU PLAY YOUR IDOL.
IT DEPENDS ON HOW I'M
FEELING.
I WOULD MAYBE RISK IT.
THAT'S HOW SURE I FEEL THEY WANT
TO TAKE HIM OUT RIGHT NOW.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW THAT'S REALLY STRESSFUL.
IF ALICIA DOESN'T VOTE OUT
TARZAN, I WILL PROBABLY VOTE
WITH ALICIA, CHRISTINA AND
TARZAN TO TAKE CHELSEA OUT.
MY STRUGGLE TO KEEP CHELS IN
THIS
GAME AND USE AN IDOL THAT TAKES
ME TO THE FINAL FOUR NO MATTER
WHAT SEEMS LIKE AN UNWISE
DECISION TO PUT EVERYTHING ON
THE LINE FOR CHELSEA AND SABRINA
WITH SIX PEOPLE LEFT IN THE GAME
WHEN I KNOW FOR A FACT I COULD
SIT AT THE FINAL FOUR.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT INFURIATES
ME?
WHAT.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT INFURIATES
ME?
WHAT.
PEOPLE LIKE THAT, THAT ARE
GOING TO BE HERE LONGER THAN ME.
WHAT?
NO, NO, NO.
HUH?
YOU'RE GOING TO GO TO THE
END.
IT'S NOT THE END OF THE ROAD AT
ALL.
( SIGHS )
THAT'S JUST WHAT BOTHERS ME.
LIKE, IF I WERE TO GO HOME
TOMORROW KNOWING CHRISTINA'S
HERE, AFTER 35 DAYS.
DON'T THINK LIKE THAT.
I SHOULDN'T THINK LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW HOW THIS GAME CAN
QUICKLY CHANGE.
LET'S JUST TAKE IT OUR BY OUR.
NOT EVEN FREAKING DAY BY DAY
NOW, HOUR BY HOUR.
THIS PLAN TONIGHT HINGES ON
PRETTY MUCH TWO PEOPLE TO SWAY
THE VOTES.
KIM TO SWAY ALICIA'S MIND TO SAY
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER AND
WE WANT THAT SUCKER TARZAN GONE.
HE IS OUT TO GET YOU.
AND IT ALL HINGES ON ALICIA
BELIEVING EVERY MORSAL OF WHAT
COMES OUT OF KIM'S MOUTH.
KIM, SHE BATS HER BABY BLUE EYES
AND LOOKS RIGHT DEAD AT YOU, AND
IT'S REALLY HARD NOT TO BELIEVE
KIM.
SEE, I'M STILL WALKING WITH
YOU, EVEN THOUGH MY FOOT IS
MESSED UP.
BUT I SENSE-- I SENSE YOU
DON'T WANT ME TO GO DOWN TO THE
TOP THREE.
NO!
YOU SURE?
I FEEL THAT--
I MEAN, YOU CAN TELL ME THE
TRUTH.
LISTEN--
NO, FILE WE NEED TO TAKE
OUT-- OW!
CHELSEA TODAY.
YES, IS KIM STILL ON BOARD
WITH THAT?
YES, I TALKED TO HER.
WE'RE ALL GOOD.
I'VE BEEN AWARE THAT THE
GIRLS NEEDED ME TO HELP THEM GET
RID OF THE BOYS.
WELL, I DID THAT.
I ACTUALLY DID THAT.
I HELP THEM GET RID OF FIVE
BOYS.
AND NOW IF I HAVEN'T SCREWED IT
UP BY BEING IRASCIBLE THE LAST
COUPLE OF DAYS, I HOPE THE GIRLS
DON'T JUMP ON ME TONIGHT BUT
ACTUALLY KNOCK OUT CHELSEA.
IF IT'S YOU, ME, AND CHRISTINA,
I THINK YOU'VE GOT IT NAILED.
IF ALICIA WOULD THINK IT THROUGH
A LITTLE BIT BETTER SHE'D SEE
WHY THAT WOULD BE BETTER FOR
HER.
EXCEPT THEY KNOW THERE'S NO WAY
FOR HER TO REALLY TRUST ME, AND
SO SHE COULD BE INFLUENCED BY
KIM.
HOW ABOUT IF WE END UP TAKING
KIM?
IF YOU TAKE KIM, I THINK
YOU'RE BEST BET AT WINNING, IF
YOU TAKE CHRISTINA.
I THINK KIM-- KIM'S, HER ANGELIC
FACE HER BLUE EYES, SHE MIGHT
TWIN AFTER ALL, AND THAT'S NOT
FAIR TO YOU.
KIM, WITH HER ANGELICKIZE,
ACTUALLY FOOLED TROYZAN AND
JAY-BIRD, SO GOOD KNOWS, SHE
COULD PROBABLY FOOL ALICIA.
HERE WE GO!
PUT IT ON.
I BET $5?
O-M-G.
THIS ISN'T OFFENSIVE TO
ANYBODY IF I WORE THIS?
THAT TANK TOP HAS DRIED BLOOD
ON IT.
ALL RIGHT.
I WOULDN'T WANT WOMEN'S DIRTY
PANTIES TOUCHING THE SKIN ON MY
FOREHEAD.
I DON'T WANT TO BLINDSIDE
TARZAN TONIGHT.
WE HAVE A FATHER-DAUGHTER-LIKE
RELATIONSHIP.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, HE MIGHT
REUNITE WITH SABRINA AND TAKE
CHRISTINE AND PERSUADE HER.
AND THOSE ARE THINGS THAT I WANT
TO AVOID.
PLEASE, PLEASE, HOLD THE
APPLAUSE.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
PLEASE.
THIS IS KILLING ME.
I WANT TO SAY I TRUST KIM.
I WANT TO SAY 100%, BUT THERE
IS, LIKE, THIS DOUBT IN MY MIND
THAT MAYBE SHE'S PLAYING ME.
SO IT'S, LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE DO
I GO WITH?
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
OH, BOY.
Jeff: JONAS, MICHAEL, JAY,
LEIF, TROYZAN, AND KAT, VOTED
OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, SABRINA, HERE WE ARE, DOWN
TO A HAND FULL, AND ARE YOU
STILL HERE.
SURPRISE YOU?
NO, NOT REALLY.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU DON'T PUT
YOURSELF IN THE MIX, THEN, YOU
KNOW, YOU'VE ALREADY DEFEATED
YOURSELF FROM THE START.
SO OF COURSE YOU HAVE TO INCLUDE
YOURSELF.
Jeff: STILL BELIEVE YOU CAN
WIN?
WHY NOT?
YEAH.
Jeff: TARZAN, YOU'RE STILL
HERE.
ONLY BY THE GRACE OF GOD I'M
STILL HERE.
Jeff: WHY DO YOU THINK YOU
ARE STILL HERE WHEN ALL THE
OTHER GUYS ARE OVER ON THE JURY?
BECAUSE I HELPED THE LADIES
GET RID OF THE GUYS.
Jeff: BUT THAT MOMENT HAS
COME AND GONE.
AND MY MOMENT'S PROBABLY JUST
ABOUT OVER.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF SOMEBODY WANTS
TO TAKE ME TO THE END, I'LL GO.
I'M NOT STUPID.
BUT IT WOULDN'T BE A BAD TACTIC
BECAUSE THESE FIVE GUYS ARE
GOING TO VOTE FOR WHAT, A
MILLIONAIRE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
Jeff: SO, SABRINA, SOMEBODY
WHO DOESN'T BELIEVE HE CAN WIN
AND NO ONE ELSE SEEMS TO BELIEVE
HE CAN WIN COULD BECOME AN
ASSET.
TO A DEGREE, BUT AT THE END
OF THE DAY, WE'RE WOMEN AND HE'S
STILL A MAN, AND NO MATTER WHO
HE HELPED PICK OFF THERE MAY BE
SOME PEOPLE ON THE JURY WHO ARE
LIKE, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T WANT A WOMAN TO WIN AT
ALL.
IT'S A RISK, I THINK, TO TAKE
HIM TO THE TOP.
Jeff: TARZAN, REALLY,
THERE'S VERY LITTLE ROOM TO
HIDE.
I THINK OUR GAME IS SOLID AT
THE MOMENT.
I MEAN, THEY'VE KEPT THEIR WORD
AND ALMOST INVARIABLY THE RIGHT
PERSON GOES EACH TIME.
Jeff: TARZAN, DO YOU THINK
THE JURY WOULD AGREE?
NO, IT'S HUMAN NATURE WHEN
YOU'RE VOTED OUT, YOU'RE NOT
INTROSPECTIVE ENOUGH TO SAY,
"WAIT A MINUTE.
THE PERSON THAT'S VOTED OUT
ISN'T IN THE ALIGNMENT WHEN THE
GAME IS-- EXCUSE ME-- AFOOT."
Jeff: BUT THEY BELIEVE THEY
WERE.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT POINT.
Jeff: TARZAN, DO YOU OFTEN
FEEL MISUNDERSTOOD IN THIS GAME?
I WOULD SAY THAT'S TRUE,
YEAH.
IT'S LIKE THE DAY I WORE
SOMETHING AND THEY'RE WORRIED
ABOUT MIGROAB CROEBS AND THEY
HAVE NO IDEA WHAT I KNOW ABOUT
THAT AND THAT'S WHY I WASN'T
WORRY BUT THEY WERE.
Jeff: WHAT DID YOU WEAR?
HE'S WEARING KAT'S TANK.
I'M WEARING THIS, BUT I ALSO
PUT HER PANTIES ON MY HEAD, AND
THEY WERE LIKE, "OH, NO!
PANTY!
"JUST FOR A JOKE.
AND I'M NOT AFRAID OF THOSE
PANTIES AT ALL.
Jeff: SABRINA, THIS REALLY
IS, ON A VERY BASE LEVEL WHAT
"SURVIVOR" IS ABOUT.
YOU HAVE TO DECIDE, TARZAN WANTS
TO PUT ON KAT'S SHIRT, HE THINKS
IT'S FUNNY.
HE STILL MIGHT BE THE GUY I TAKE
TO THE END.
THOSE ARE THE DECISION YOU
WEIGH.
AND WHAT I'VE BEEN WEIGHING
IS COULD THIS BRILLIANT MAN WHO
IS WEARING PANTIES ON HIS HEAD
BE PLAYING US.
OH, I JUST WANTED TO SEE MY
WEAPON WIFE.
I JUST WANT THE THE ADVENTURE.
AND NOW YOU WANT TO PLAY THE
GAME... YEAH.
Jeff: ALICIA WHAT THE
REACTION BACK TO CAMP WHEN
SABRINA AND KIM WERE ASKED TO GO
WITH CHELSO THE AWARD.
SHE PICKED SABRINA, WHO I
THOUGHT WAS A FAIR CHOICE,
DEFINITELY.
HOWEVER, WAS KIM A FAIR CHOICE,
WHEN THESE TWO HAVE NOT BEEN ON
ANY REWARDS IN A WHILE?
I MEAN, THAT'S KIND OF UP TO THE
PERSON WHO IS PICKING.
KAT PICKED TWO PEOPLE THAT SHE
LIKED --
AND SHE WAS VOTED OUT.
RIGHT.
Jeff: KRISTINA, FRUSTRATED
THAT CHELSEA DIDN'T PICK YOU?
YEAH, THERE WAS A LITTLE BIT
OF FRUSTRATION AND STUFF.
THERE WAS A CONVERSATION BETWEEN
CHELS AND I, AND WE MADE AN
AGREEMENT THAT, LIKE, WE WOULD
TAKE EACH OTHER.
SO I WAS A LITTLE BIT
DISAPPOINTED.
BUT --
SO YOU FEEL LIKE SHE BROKE
HER WORD TO YOU.
YES, I DID.
SHE ALSO BROKE HER WORD TO ME
RIGHT AFTER THAT CONVERSATION
WHICH IS WHY I DIDN'T TAKE HER.
Jeff: SO WHAT WILL SAVE YOU
TONIGHT?
I THINK PEOPLE ARE STARTING
TO GET A BIGGER FEEL FOR TARZAN
AND WHAT HE REALLY MIGHT BE
DOING IN THIS GAME.
I DON'T THINK IT'S JUST AN
ADVENTURE FOR HIM.
I THINK HE MIGHT BE PLAYING SOME
PEOPLE MORE THAN THEY THINK.
JEFF, I'M NOT PLAYING
ANYBODY.
AND THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY
ABOUT IT.
Jeff: ON THAT NOTE, LET'S
GET TO THE VOTE.
CANNOT VOTE FOR ALICIA.
SHE HAS IMMUNITY.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
TARZAN, YOU'RE UP.
TARZAN, PLEASE GET THE HELL
OFF THIS ISLAND BEFORE YOU DRIVE
ME CRAZY.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTE.
FIRST VOTE, CHELSEA.
TARZAN.
TWO VOTES TARZAN, ONE VOTE
CHELSEA.
TARZAN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES TARZAN, ONE
VOTE CHELSEA.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SEVENTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
TARZAN.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
TARZAN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
I WANT TO THANK YOU LADIES
AND YOU GENTLEMEN FOR THE
ADVENTURE AND FOR ALLOWING ME TO
SEE MY WIFE.
ADIOS.
Jeff: ADIOS, TARZAN.
THANKS, TARZAN.
Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE DONE IT.
ALL THE MEN ARE GONE.
MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON A
SPECIAL TWO-HOUR SEASON FINALE.
13 HAVE FALLEN, ONLY FIVE WOMEN
REMAIN.
THIS IS STILL ANYONE'S GAME.
GO!
COME ON, BABY!
Jeff: WHO WILL OUTLAST ALL
THE REST AND BECOME THE SOLE
SURVIVOR?
SUNDAY, MAY 13.
TO WIN "SURVIVOR" IS THE
GOAL.
IF A MILLION BUCKS LIFTS YOUR
SOUL.
YOU MUST OUTWIT, OUTPLAY,
OUTLAST, OR BE A SAVAGE, SOON
OUTCAST.
EXPECT THERE WILL BE SO MUCH TO
SEE, PEOPLE WILL LIE AND THEY
WILL CHEAT.
AND I'M GOING TO ADD ONE OTHER
(YELLING)