Previously on "survivor."
go,go,go!
This season's battle Of the
sexes hasn't been a Battle at all.
The men's tribe has won every Challenge.
With confidence at an all-time High,
matt and his alliance of Muscle
thought they were running The show.
it's the dominant alliance Clearly.
But the rest of the Tribe
had plans of their own.
Colton,life,tarzan,jonas and
Troizan formed an unlikely Alliance.
***
At the last immunity challenge,The
women's biggest obstacle was Cat
and with that cat jumped in For
no reason,completely Falling apart.
And the men won their
third Challenge in a row.
Men win immunity!
Back at camp,cat only made Matters worse
by wearing her Emotions on her sleeve.
it was so hard--
don't overthink it.
cat is very young and Emotional
and that's a Liability.
At tribal council it Was clear that
cat's alliance Could do without her.
Chelsea if you could start over Do you think
you guys would form Different alliances?
yeah,it would probably be Different.
In the end cat was Saved
when they voted out nina,
The oldest member of the tribe,Believed
to be a liability in Challenges.
Time for you to go.
Well,we are only five days in,And
you've yet to win a Challenge.
You've got to get it together.
16 are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
***
kitty-kat,give me a hug.
don't cry at tribal council.
didn't mean to.I didn't.I sucked it up.
all eyes are on kat right Now.
We're just starting to look at The weaker
players,even they're In our alliance.
what a joke.
Our next move is just to try
to Stay as positive as possible.
If we just get the
smallest Glimmer of hope,
I think it will Challenge the whole tribe,just
A little bit of confidence is All we need.
- Do y'all want to come
over to Our-- you scared me.
this is a massive ass storm Coming in.
♪♪
***
we might be running our
Little tails doin there.
we'll see how bad it gets Over here.
- good night,girls.
- good night.
it just got cold.
just came up out of nowhere.
this is going to be Horrendous.
colton just came by and
said If the weather gets bad
we could Down there and try
to sleep Under their shelters.
guys,I say we tough it out.
We'll be fine.
oh my god!
It's freezing.
The wind is coming
straight Through here.
I felt raindrops.
oh,my god,I feel rain,too.
the men,they have a tarp.
But we don't,and it was Raining.
And right now,I feel like our
Whole shelter is about to blow Down.
oh,my gosh.
It's so cold.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=- proudly presents
Survivor  Season 24Episode
03 one world
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí
***
oh my gosh
we've been crapped on
since We've been here.
We got zero sleep last night.
We stayed up the entire night.
Froze soak wet.
And we haven't had fire because It rained
and put it out,so now We haven't eaten.
where is the sun?
Hey,boys.
where are you going?
Where are you going?
they said my name.
oh,come on!
you don't have fire,do you?
- do I have fire?
- yeah.
Is your's all out.
we have fire?
is it still going?
Are you guys soaked?
Totally soaked.
can we go by your fire and Dry out?
sure,go over there.
Go right now.
It's going right now.
It's fine.
I just want to be warm
for,Like,one minute.
I can't be cold one more Second.
I was thankful last night That we stuck
to our guns a Little bit after tribal
and Didn't run over and
jump in the Men's shelter.
But going over this this
Morning,I have no shame.
I've never been so miserable.
I couldn't get my tail over
There to that fire fast enough.
come on,come on,guys.
oh,hey,guys.
Didn't see you guys coming.
♪♪
sorry,guys.
I hope this is a temporary
Pit stop at the men's camp.
I don't think any of the
girls Want to stand over there.
It's uncomfortable mooching off Of them.
They're all like,excuse me.
♪♪
***
look at my fingers.
that's crazy.
it's ridiculous.
what's up?
good morning.
I went out crab hunting
this Morning,and came back,
and Found the girls in our
shelter Underneath our stuff,
sitting on Our beds,soaking
wet,you know,Sitting by our fire.
I get it,they had a tough Night.
I think some of the guys
are Sensitive to that,
but there's Barely room for nine guys in
That shelter and there's no Extra room,
and that means for The
girls,their day is done.
Come on in,guys!
You guys ready to get to
today's Reward challenge.
yes.yes.
Here's wow it works.
One at a time tribe members
will Square off in a memory test.
I'm going to show you a series
Of items in a specific order.
When you've memorized them,You'll
pull a lever,drop a Curtain,
then race to recreate The
same series in the same Order.
First person to get it right
Scores a point for their tribe.
First tribe to five wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing For?
yes.
A complete fishing Supply kit and a canoe
with Paddles waiting for you back at Camp.
In addition,clearly,you
are Playing for momentum.
Guys,you have two extra
men,Sitting two people out.
♪♪
***
****
all***
s******
so****
♪♪
and****
you*****
here***
wow****
it***
let***
matt***
s***
woman**
colton**
Here we go.
colton****
♪♪
let**
he***
see***
m*****
***
next**
Who are you jay.
The men have yet to score.
Here we go.
Once again,six items.
Wow,alicia was quick out
o of e Gate on that one.
Alicia not messing around.
Alicia going to commit.
Who gets to the mat first?
Alicia gets to the
mat just Ahead of jay.
The women are right again.
Women lead 3-zip.
Next two,come up on.
Kat taking on troyzahn,last
Round was six items.
We're going to bump it up.
Eight items.
what?
don't worry about it.
Troyzahn,not even close.
The men continue to be pathetic In this.
The women don't have it right,Either.
Re-rack and we'll go again.
Here we go.
Troyzahn is not right.
Kat is not right.
Re-rack and we go again.
Kat thinks she has it right.
No.Men have it wrong as well.
Re-rack,we go again.
She is wrong.
He is wrong.
No,wrong.
No,re-rack.Re-rack.Go
again.
For the seventh
time,troyzahn Versus kat.
Kat would like to extend
the Lead for the women.
Troyzan hoping he can put the Men
on the board,kat not Messing around.
She's back very quickly.
It doesn't matter,troyzan,kat
Has it right for the women.
Women are dominating.
They lead 4-zip.
Next two,come on up.
Christina versus bill.
Here's where we stand.
Men have not even
gotten on the Board,bill.
If you lose this Challenge is over.
that's it?
Okay,okay.
You must win to keep The men alive.
Let's go.
Women can win it right here.
Bill has already taken off.
Bill wants to keep
the men alive In this.
He's going to have to beat Christina.
Christina would like to
close it Out right now.
Go home with the women's
first Victory in this game.
Christina coming back. Bill coming back.
Christina was back first.
Thinks she has it right.
She does.
Women win reward!
Ladies,nice work.
Get your reward.
The canoe will be waiting
for You back at camp.
You do not need to share it.
It is your canoe.
But one thing has changed as a
Result of this morning's Challenge
it's women now know They
can beat you at something.
We'll see how it plays out.
Grab your stuff,head back to Camp.
***
oh,my god!There's our boat!
so awesome.
We've knot a boat.
we won our first challenge.
It was absolutely amazing,Definitely
what we needed to Pick up the tribe.
We came back to this horrible Weather.
c****
the plan is to get the
fire Going,fix our shelter,
you Know,keep everybody warm,Because
right now we're on the Verge of,
you know,a horrible Storm right now.
♪♪
I don't know what else to do.
Good grief.
***
I wonder how long this is Going to last.
all right,guys,we have
a Big question for you.
yeah.
all of our coconuts are wet.
We're trying to start a fire.
We can't do the magnesium bar
Because the inside is damp.
Is there any way we can
possibly Have an ember?
can we take out the canoe Sometimes.
we can't make a decision
Without everybody else?
you guys were all here Hanging around the
fire this Morning and that was a big deal.
guys,we have rain
pouring in Our shelter.
we do,too.
thank you so much.
I appreciate it.
We're not trying to be Unreasonable.
I'm freezing.
they have to give us Something,man.
Otherwise all this
stuff is Going to stop.
some of the guys are like we
Have to stop giving them stuff
And not getting anything in
Return which I do agree with.
I love some of those girls but
If they're not giving us Things--
I am a republican,I am Note a democrat.
I do not believe in handouts.
it is raining really hard,And my
hands are incredibly Waterlogged.
My feet are probably worse.
I haven't looked at those yet.
we're just miserable right Now.
And hopefully the rain
lets up a Little bit.
if this was a life-or-death
Situation,obviously,we would Help them.
I would help humans out.
this is a game.
- Every time we give them fire--
we're not here to ask for Anything.
no,we just want to get warm.
y'all don't have fire yet?
sorry,I'm just so drenched I Need,
like five seconds out of Rain and
then I will be out of Your way.
the girls are beyond a mess.
They're,like,zombies,you
Know,like shivering.
And I'm,like,let them tough it Out.
the boat's really cool.
we plan on taking it out one Day soon.
- When y'all aren't using it?
- you are?
I don't know.
didn't you just walk away
With fire a while ago?
aren't you standing here Right now?
yes or no.Yes or no.
Really,straight up.
I'm just going to be honest.
I just don't think your deals Are fair.
you wouldn't be able to cook
Anything if it weren't for us.
I don't even want to hear it.
we're not ask to borrow.
We're asking if we can use it.
I thing is,I can't make a Decision
unless I let them all Know.
- awlime saying-- I will let
them know that's What you want.
Don't come at me like I'm crazy.
You don't need to take
it all That serious.
I'm just saying.
oh,no vote,after everything We've given
to you,that's how It's going to be?
So when you want fire,when you Want shelter,you use
your Womenly charms to take care of Those situations.
But when we ask for a boat,you Say no?
One world is out the window.
go back and discuss our plan With them.
Go back and ask about the
deal And see what they say.
And then come back with a
Consensus,and then we'll settle It.
all right.
she's an idiot.
they think it's like-- you know what they come
Across as spoiled kind of like,"where's my stuff?
Where's my fire?
Come build me.Come help me.
" I don't understand,like,What
they're thinking.
well,maybe that's the thing.
We're men,they're women.
They think different.
no,because even I don't Understand.
those boys said since
they Gave us that ember--
ember,they want us to
let Them use the canoe.
they want to take the canoe Out and we better
discuss it or They're about to take it out.
that wasn't negotiated at All.
They
said--
I needed just five seconds
to Try to dry my hands out,
and all They did was bitch
at us,like-- what happened.
we still need things
so,Here,we don't have the wood--
I would give them all our
Fishing gear and that freak,Boat.
I just want to sleep on one
Freaking night before I lose my Mind.
I'm losing it.
Like,I'm so freaking cold.
we're just--
we're girls.
We're just not meant to
be,Like,beaten down this well.
***
let***
this morning,th sun finally Came up so we
feel like we need To put our reward to use
and Learn to spear fish
and get our Confidence in
that so we know we Can go out
and catch a fish if We're hungry.
good job!
I got it.It's little but
at least it's Something.
it's a little surprising how
Things are kind of turning Around.
It feels awesome.
All three of us went out and
we All three caught a fish.
They weren't very big but we did It.
good work,girls!
things are starting to feel Different.
I feel like people get why They're fear.
Before it felt like where am I?
What am I doing?
you caught a fish you did
That from the boat?
I think the girls are
feeling More confident.
You know,they got their feet Under them.
congratulations.
and it's going to change the
Way we feel,the guys feel.
You know,we need to win again
Come on in,guys!
You guys ready to get to
today's Immunity challenge?
yeah.yeah!
First things first,I Will take
it back again from the Men.
- Leif.
- you're welcome.
Once again,immunity
Is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,one
Person will be your caller.
The other six tribe members
will Be blindfolded into pairs.
Using only verbal commands,the Caller will
lead the pairs Through a series of obstacles.
You'll make your way to a water
Tower,pull the rope releasing The water,
and along with it a
Bag of puzzle pieces.
Once you have all five bags,the Caller will
then use those Pieces to solve a puzzles.
First tribe to get it right wins
Immunity,avoids tribal council,
Losers,somebody will
be going Home tonight.
Men,you have two extra members.
Who is going to sit out?
Colton and jay.
Take a spot on the bench.
good luck,guys.
Everybody else,I'll Give you a minute
to strategize,We'll get started.
All right,we have our
callers,Bill for the men.
Sabrina for the women.
Survivors ready?For immunity.
Go!
monica,diagonal.
left,forward.
monica,turn around,stop,Stop.
Go straight.
Run,monica,run.
straight.
alicia,go straight.
sidestep,sidestep.
monica,monica,stop.
No,no,no.
Ladies-- get on
your knees and Crawl.
matt to your right,to your Right!
Reach forward.
It's right there.
Yes.
The men have their First bucket and their first
bag Of puzzle pieces and they're Heading back.
Alicia and kat looking
for their First bucket.
she's not even directing us.
sabrina!
Christina and monica.
get back up.
they just took a big hit.
jonas and leif,turn to your Right.
It's right there!
Jonas and leif have The
second bag of puzzle pieces.
reach up!
Tarzan and troyzan Looking
for their third bucket.
reach around! Reach around!
Reach forward! Reach forward!
Reach up! Reach around! Keep reaching!
sabrina! Sabrina.
Tarzan and troyzan Consider
their third bag of Puzzle pieces.
Alicia and cat have the first Bag
of puzzle pieces for the Women.
yes!
Matt and mike have The fourth
bag of puzzle pieces For the men.
to your right!
troyzan,keep coming.
sabrina!
monica,go straight up.
Monica and christina,Looking for
some help and not Getting any.
straight up the pole?
where?
chelsea turn around and reach Up.
Chelsea,right behind up.
Troyzan and tarzan Back with the
fourth bag of Puzzle pieces for the men.
go to your right,mike!
Chelsea and kim have The
second bag for the women.
up! Up! Matt,reach up!
All right,bring it back!
The men have the Fifth and final bag.
turn around,kat.
They've just got to Get back to the course
and bill Can start working on the puzzle.
Alicia and kat have the
third Bag for the women.
The women need to keep moving.
Alicia and kat heading
back with The second bag.
Matt and mike heading back with
The fifth and final bag for the Men.
Chelsea and kim heading
back With the third bag.
dop it over!
The men have all five Bags.
Bill heading down now to start Work.
Men,take off your blindfolds.
monica,go straight!
over the pole?
no! Monica!
First,bill has to Untie the bags.
Empty the puzzle pieces.
You've got a big lead right now.
go straight down.
The women still Struggling,looking
for their Fourth and fifth bag.
sabrina,which way?
Bill starting to work On the puzzle.
He has a lot of time and
doesn't Need to panic.
you're al almost there.
Go up.
Kim and chelsea have The
fourth bag for the women.
Still one more bag out there.
Monica and christina
still Empty-handed.
The women could have a shot
if They could get these piece.
yeah,keep that.
That looks good.
Chelsea and kim Coming back
with the fourth bag Now.
Still one bag out there.
come on,monica!
Stand up,monica.
Go to your left.
Start reaching up,baby.
Go.
The women have their
Fifth and final bag.
They need to get those
pieces And get back here!
You need to move,women!
go to your right.
Bill taking his time,Wisely so.
He has a huge lead and a big
Learning curve on this puzzle.
The women still have to get back
And figure out how this puzzle Works.
Huge advantage for the men,Time-wise.
to your right,to your right.
The women have their
Fifth and final bag.
Sabrina can head down now.
She's got a lot of time to make Up.
Women have been to tribal
Council every single week.
They do not want to go again.
bill,find a spot,one at a Time.
the very bottom.
Long,skinny.
Sabrina quickly gets
To work on this puzzle.
Where do these pieces fit?
How do they go?
thatta boy.
Bill gets another Piece for the men.
and it goes right there.
perfect.
Sabrina has her first
Piece for the women.
bill,you have lots of
time And a big lead.
Bill with another Piece.
The men with a ligged about Right now.
that's the one.
Sabrina gets the Second
piece in this puzzles.
The women would love to have
a Break from tribal council.
Sabrina with a third piece now.
yeah,yeah,yeah.
hold on,hold on.
The men have a huge Advantage.
Can the women close the gap Right flow?
Sabrina with the fourth
piece For the women.
Men still with the lead.
Sabrina with the fifth
piece for The women.
Women starting to gain.
does it slide in?
nope.
other side.
The women have six Pieces now.
They have tied it up.
Sabrina has brought the women Back.
Both tribes with four pieces Left.
Bill with the seventh piece for The men.
slides into the purple,right Below you.
The women really Helping
out,working well Together.
We're tied again.
Bill is starting to sweat a Little bit.
Had a big lead.
Dead even.
Three pieces left.
bill with the eighth piece For the men.
The women have their Eighth piece.
that is going to be orange.
does this go in here?
The women have the Ninth piece.
Sabrina down to her last
piece,Where does it go?
Bill is down to his last piece.
Where does it go?
This is it.
The women have made a huge Comeback.
It's a showdown,right
now.One piece left.
The women win Immunity!
With a huge comeback!
I think I just aged 10 years.
Women,Congratulations.
A huge come-from-behind
victory.
No tribal council Tonight.
Enjoy the night off.
Head back to camp and celebrate.
yes!
All right,guys.
Tribal council tonight.
Somebody will be voted out of This game.
You will lose your first tribe Member.
Grab your stuff.Head back to camp.
I'll see you at tribal.
my mind was just blown.
I couldn't believe we lost.
But now that we've lost this Challenge,I'm
looking forward To doing this.
I mean I've spent eight days
out Here creating some power
and I Want to use it and I want
to Execute some of if tonight.
That's what's going to happen.
***
that was awesome!
where are we going to put Them?
good work!
oh,my god.
was that a come from behind Or what?
today I was worried because It was a
communication-type Challenge,but we pulled Through.
I know.
thanks,leif.
what's funny sthawkd tell the Boys thought they
had it in the Bag because they were so far Ahead.
And so now they're probably just All running
around like chickens With their heads cut off,
not Knowing what to do.
***
bill?
yes,sir.
did you a great job.
yeah,good job.
thanks,guys,I appreciate It.
I lost my voice on that--
on That calling for sure.
I'm so excited to vote Someone out.
I dislike so many of these People.
Like,bill,screwed up
in the Challenge today.
I'm sorry,you had a good,like,
Five- to seven-minute lead over
Those women,and you still lost.
dude,that's a knot in there,Dude.
Open it.
That's just mock,bro.
I can't deal with it.
"yo,bro. Bro." Shut up.
Go kill yourself.
All he's doing it dig himself a Grave.
you're going fishing!
I came right at that precise Time.
It's so amazing.
I don't want to talk to you.
I don't like you,stay away from Me.
You're ghetto trash.
That's all you are.
I can't stand him,ugggg,and
I Want him gone,yesterday.
Okay,this right
here,one,two,Three,four,five.
This is our five,solidified.
absolutely.
Plus a floater.
who is our floater?
you know,bill.
is going first.
- oh,really?
- yeah.
what happened?
he's too wishy-washy.
okay,but why don't we make Him second.
Matt say real danger.
bill is the type that will Slip
up behind you and slit your Throat.
and we all know that,don't We?
you need to eliminate that,First.
right now there are clearly
Two sides in our tribe.
There's matt,mike,jay,and Bill.
And then there's me and
jonas,Tarzan,leif,and colton.
We've got the numbers,so
the Guys in the alliance
basically Are the ones who
are picking who Is going home.
If it's going to be
matt,it's Going to be matt.
If they switch it and say it's Going
to be bill,it's going to Be bill.
And really the one making the
Biggest suggestion is colton.
everybody's out chatting.
I figured I'd come see what
Everybody is chatting about.
And it got quiet when I walked
Up so I can only assume--
well,we're not voting
you Out,so don't worry.
is it you guys right here?
it might be.
Do you want to be with us?
We all like you?
I think you just backthe Wrong horse.
that's why wriewr not-- That's why
wriewr you're not on The ticket right now.
Can you make a decision
while You're standing there.
jay bird.
if they have the numbers and I'm not a
part of that,that Puts a target on my back,
so I Can either join them
or butt Heads with them,
so I basically Had no options and
said,"okay,I'll vote with you guys.
" it seems like the consensus
Is bill at the moment.
that the name.
I'm cool with that?
- Are you cool with that?
- yeah.
the best guy would have been Matt,but we're a
team,if you Guys want to do bill,we'll do Bill.
here comes matt.
what's all the deep thought About?
we're-- we're-- to be
honest,We're talking strategies.
okay.
I mean,obviously,right?
- seems pretty obvious.
- yeah.
is my presence destroying
the Strategy talk?
no. yes,it is,at the moment.
Well it is.
I walked up intentionally on
These guys having a Conversation.
Clearly right in front
of me About strategy,
so I just wanted To stick my
head in it and shake It up.
I don't like people talking
like That when I'm not involved.
I walked up there and it got Quiet.
I'll leave you boys be.
I walked away,no problem.
What I did want to
do is pull Troy aside.
you want to talk alone?
yeah.
troy and I spent the last Week as the heads
of two snakes That are battling each other.
You're either with me and
my Guys or you're with troy.
And I've decided that
something Had to be said.
well,there was-- this Concept of
let's get rid of all The muscle.
It's voant,just like it's Convenient
for all the muscle to Band together.
of course.
but it's easy.
I think we've got to come up
With a smaller group of guys.
right.that we intend on diving
deep Into this game with.
Me,you,jay,maybe
mike,maybe One other guy.
All of us are roosters and we Don't
want any other roosters With me.
The chickens,they can't
break Up the roosters.
And that's how I saw it from day One
and,frankly,I saw you as Part of the roosters.
I would love to create a new Reality and let
all the idiots Scramble and get rid of colton.
the guys in power are going To vote
for colton and when we Get back to camp
they're going To realize the average
joes are Not calling the shots
and things Have changed around here
and I'm Still in the front of of it.
♪♪
***
****
We're in an alliance and we'll Like
I am never going to be With you.
It ain't "survivor" unless You're lying.
he wants me,mike,jay,and Jonas.
As an alliance.
Matt is so dangerous to me,Dude.
It's like,when he talks he's
Like,"this is what we've got to Do.
And I'm tired of the
smiewl Little people.
Us roosters walk around--" and He
included me with the rooster Group.
I think matt is
so power Hungry--
you think we should get rid Of
matt before we get rid of Bill?
well,everybody wants to vote For bill.
right now,the vote is
Between bill and matt.
If I had my way bill would
go Because he's annoying
and I hate Him and I hate his voice
and I Can't stand to listen to him Talk.
Matt,on the other hand,is
like The hltd of the snake
and you Have to chop off the headst
Snake for the rest of it to Stop-
whatsoever--
wiggling.
are you ready to go,boss?
oh,my god.
Either one makes me perfectly Happy.
Honestly,out of this tribe
of Nine,if I could get rid of,
Like,five people,it would be Heaven.
Behind each of you is A torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch
and Approach the flame.
Dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual at
Tribal council because in this Game,
fire represents your life.
When your fire is gone,so are You.
So,michael,with nine guys,There has
to be a little bit of A power struggle,
at least Initially.
you know,the dynamics
just Kind of came together.
Like,me and matt clicked Instantly.
He's somebody you can work with.
But there are a lot of different
Alliances gog in this tribe.
It's hard to keep track of.
Tarzan,so only eight Games within this game
there are Fractions within this group of Nine.
as far as I'm concerned,we Have an
alliance of five and I Trust those five.
And I think we'll stick Together.
That's what I believe.
So,colton,if There's an alliance of five That's
strong,math says the Other four would be in trouble.
well,I'm not uncomfortable
Because I'm not going home Tonight.
And why is that?
because I have an idol.
The girls gave it to me.
So you're saying You're not going
home because You're going to play it--
yeah.
I'm not going to be a james.
I'm not going to have
an idol And go home.
That's stupid.
Michael,is there a Thought that
an idol at camp is Too disruptive
so let's throw Some votes just
to make sure we Get it out.
that's on a lot of our minds.
Colton,he's colton.
This whole time he's
worked with Two tribes.
He was sleeping over there,Eating
over there and we didn't Know
which way it was going and
Then he has an idol on our side
So it's disrupting the whole Game.
Colton,you've been Spending
a lot of time with the Women.
well,yeah,that shouldn't be A shock.
Wait,a second,why
Shouldn't that be a shock?
Are you on the men's tribe.
all of my friends at home are Girls.
You're not on their Tribe.
You don't compete with them.
You don't go to tribal council,And
so you look at me and say,
"duuh.Tts a severse
duuh,double dare On you.
here's the thing,women are
More,like,nurturing and they Pet and you
they tell you,you
Know,it's going to be okay.
Do you realize what Kind of a target
you put on your Back when you say that?
well,yeah,but that Distribute mean
I'm going to Vote with those women.
Bill,explain to me How this makes sense.
I mean,honestly,as much as He
assumed that we spot on Judged him.
He spot on judged us and assumed
We wouldn't take him in --
you mean,because he's gay?
yeah.
Tarzan.
here's what we discovered.
Colton's highly intelligent.
He's invaluable with regard to
Understanding how this game Plays.
He already has allegiances with Females over
there,and when we Combine,he's already said.
He's real smart.
If we value our sevival we need
Him in the first few plays here.
who is "we," tarzan.
I'm talk ago I used the
word "we" in a general sense.
I'm trying to help
colton defend His status
because I believe He's very valuable
and I think Our team will prosper
if he Stays here a bit longer.
And,matt,you're not Buying it.
well,I think tarzan has,you
Know,put out a cry for help to
Whoever it is the five
guys who Are with him.
And it does seem like tarzan is
Shivering in his boots over Here,
and I'm just getting sick Of him using
vague terms and Want him to talk turkey.
you're absolutely wrong.
That's not the motive
behind What I'm saying.
I'm not buying it.
my heart is broken that
he Misinterprets me.
Matt,are you Enjoying this game?
Because you seem a little Agitated.
well,yeah,some of the Things that have been
said here Tonight agitate me,mainly Tarzan.
Tarzan is always talking.
Everybody is always lawftion at Tarzan but
you don't know who is Taking him seriously.
I want people to listen
and take Me seriously.
Do you think people Take you seriously?
I do.
How will tonight's Vote
change this game for you?
we all get one chance to make Hay move that
sets the ball in Motion,and that's tonight.
I think the game does
change all The time.
You always have to be willing to Reassess
and always be changing What you're doing.
Bill,how concerned Are you that tonight's
vote will Not go the way you want it to Go?
you know,it's all fun and Games
until you're right here,Right now.
I mean,like,this is intense,Man.
This is emotion right here.
You know what I mean?
Like,we're sitting here.
Nobody knows who is going to go Home.
I'm on the edge of my
seat to See what happens.
I'm so jacked up right now.
I might go home.
I might not.
But I am so happy I got
to play This game,man.
Like,this is real intense and
There's nothing else like this,Man.
I'm so ready to do this.
All right,with that,It is time to vote.
Jonas,you're up.
♪♪
I'll go tally the Votes.
If anybody has the hidden Immunity
idol and you want to Play it,
now would be the time To do so.
Once the votes are
read,the Decision is final.
The person voted out will be Asked to
leave the tribal Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote,colton.
Bill.
Matt.
That's one vote matt,one
vote Colton,one vote bill.
Matt.
Two votes matt.
That's three votes matt.
Matt.
That's four votes matt.
One vote colton,one vote bill.
Third person voted out
of "survivor: One world.
" Matt,that's five.That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Matt,the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
First vote,first blindside.
Game on.
Grab your torches.Head back to camp.
Good night.
- jeff? Can I ask a question?
- What?
- can we hear the last two Votes?
- No.
save those questions for me.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=- proudly presents
Survivor  Season 24Episode
03 one world
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí
***
we have a betrayal.
oh,my-- the monano tribe
has lost Their marbles.
you will be first to go in Such
an egregious breech of Faith.
that's a hasty decision.
I'm thinking what?
you got that.
no.I want him gone.
I told you to pick a side
and You picked the wrong side.
I want his head on a platter.
one out,you know,eight days Is
an incredible disappointment.
You know I came out here with Big
expectations and a plan to Do it
and it didn't work out for Me.
But I thought in the last couple Of
days I had reworked something With troy
to get the numbers Back in my
favor,and clearly,I Was wrong.
I was probably as a fashion blogger,I
love when I get to do a morning talk show.