Jeff: I'M FLYING OVER A
REMOTE POLYNESIAN ISLAND.
BELOW ME ARE 18 AMERICANS WHO
HAVE ALREADY BEGUN THE ADVENTURE
OF A LIFETIME.
THIS IS DEFINITELY MY GAME.
GIRLS LOVE ME.
AS FAR AS GUYS, LIKE, THE GUYS
AREN'T GOING TO SEE ME AS A
THREAT.
FIFIND OUT ONE OF THESE DUDES
LIKE ME, OH, THEY'RE GOING TO
GET PLAYED.
I HAVE A TON OF OUTDOOR
SKILLS THAT PEOPLE WON'T
NECESSARILY KNOW BECAUSE HOW BAD
ASS COULD A SUSHI CHEF BE?
Jeff: THEY THINK THEY'VE
GOT "SURVIVOR" FIGURED OUT.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO MAKE A
GIRL ALLIANCE.
Jeff: THEY THINK THEY KNOW
THE RULES.
I'VE SEEN THE GAME CHANGE.
I THINK I'M READY FOR A TWIST.
Jeff: THEY THINK THEY'VE
SEEN EVERYTHING BUT THEY'RE IN
FOR A HUGE SURPRISE.
WHAT THEY DON'T KNOW IS THIS
SEASON, THEY'LL BE DIVIDED INTO
TWO TRIBES AND WILL LIVE
TOGETHER ON ONE BEACH.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR: ONE WORLD."
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER, TWO
TRIBES, ONE CAMP, NO RULES.
WHO WILL STAY TRUE TO THEIR
TRIBE, AND WHO WILL FORM
ALLIANCES WITH THE ENEMY?
IT IS THE ULTIMATE ADVENTURE.
39 DAYS, 18 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR.
Jeff: COME ON DOWN.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR."
( CHEERS )
YEAH!
FINALLY!
YES.
Jeff: WOMAN AT THE END WITH
THE HAT, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
KOURTNEY.
Jeff: YOU LOOK AROUND AT
THE OTHER WOMEN, WHERE DO YOU
FIT IN, IN THIS GROUP?
NOWHERE AT ALL.
Jeff: IS THAT A GOOD THING
OR A BAD THING?
DEPEND ON WHAT I MAKE OF IT,
REALLY.
Jeff: AND WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO MAKE OF IT?
WELL, I'M GOING TO MAKE IT A
GOOD THING FOR SURE.
Jeff: GUY IN THE GREEN
WHAT'S YOUR NAME.
COLTON.
Jeff: COLTON.
YEAH.
Jeff: WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THE OTHER GUYS ON THIS GROUP?
THERE IS SOME GOOD-LOOKING
GUYS.
( LAUGHTER ).
THEY'RE NOT AS GOOD LOOKING AS
ME, BUT THEY'RE GOOD LOOKING.
Jeff: OKAY, GUY RIGHT HERE
IN THE COLORFUL SHIRT.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME.
TARZAN?
Jeff: BIRTH NAME?
GREG TARZAN.
Jeff: WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
GO BY?
TARZAN.
Jeff: SO, COLTON, RIGHT
AWAY THAT'S A BIG STATEMENT,
CALL ME TARZAN ON A SHOW CALLED
"SURVIVOR."
AND HE WANTS TO SWING AND GET
ME COCONUTS, BY ALL MEANS
( LAUGHTER )
ONE GUY IS CALLED TARZAN.
I'M LIKE HE CAN'T BE TARZAN, I'M
TROYZAHN.
THIS IS MY ISLAND, BABY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO BEGIN AN ADVENTURE THAT
WILL CHANGE YOUR LIVES?
YES.
Jeff: LET'S DIVIDE INTO
TRIBES.
WOMEN OVER HERE, MEN OVER HERE.
THESE ARE THE TRIBES.
UH-OH.
Jeff: IT IS MEN VERSUS
WOMEN.
I WAS ABSOLUTELY HORRIFIED
WHEN JEFF SAID, "MEN OVER HERE,
WOMEN OVER THERE."
I WAS JUST LIKE ARE YOU FREAKING
SERIOUS?
LIKE, LOOK AT MY TRIBE AND LOOK
AT ME.
LIKE I'M THE GIRL WITHIN THE GUY
TRIBE.
Jeff: SO RIGHT AWAY THE
WOMEN ALL WENT OVER AND SAID
HELLO, THEY'RE EXCITED, THEY'RE
SMILING.
THE GUYS ARE GOING, "NO WOMAN!"
WELL, WE ALL KNOW MEN CAN'T
SURVIVE WITHOUT WOMAN.
THANK YOU!
AMEN, AMEN.
Jeff: GUY RIGHT HERE IN THE
WHITE HAWAIIAN SHIRT.
YOU'RE SHAKING YOUR HEAD.
THOSE WOMEN ARE PURELY ALL
TALK RIGHT NOW.
JUST PURE GAME.
THE GUYS WILL HAVE NO PROBLEM.
SURE...
Jeff: WITH WHAT?
WITH EVERYTHING.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MEN, YOUR
TRIBE NAME IS MANONO.
YOUR TRIBE COLOR IS ORANGE.
WOMEN, YOUR TRIBE NAME IS
SALANI.
YOUR TRIBE COLOR IS BLUE.
BEFORE I SEND YOU ON YOUR
ADVENTURE, I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
60 SECONDS TO STRIP EVERYTHING
YOU CAN OFF THIS TRUCK.
GOT IT?
YOUR TIME STARTS NOW.
GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: 60 SECONDS.
DROP IT TO ME.
Jeff: DROP YOUR ITEMS RIGHT
OUT HERE IN FRONT.
TOSS IT TO ME.
OKAY, RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT HERE!
GOT IT, GOT IT!
I GOT IT, I GOT IT, I GOT IT.
Jeff: YOU BETTER WATCH WHY
YOU WERE ITEMS
15 SECONDS.
THE GAME IS DEFINITELY ALREADY
BEGUN.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
THAT'S IT!
OFF THE TRUCK.
WE SCORED.
I STOLE THEIR STUFF.
WHERE IS THAT AXE THAT WE
GOT?
I GRABBED IT, I GRABBED IT.
Jeff: LET'S ASSESS THE
TAKE.
I GOT THE AXE.
Jeff: WOMEN YOU SEEM TO
HAVE SOME COCONUTS IN THE BACK
AND SOME BANANAS IN THE FRONT.
AND AN AXE SOMEWHERE.
.
I THINK IT WAS TAKEN?
THEY TOOK OUR AXE?
YOU GUYS ARE CHEATS.
WE DIDN'T TAKE NOTHING.
I BROUGHT AN AXE OVER HERE SO
SOMEBODY CAME ON OUR TERRITORY
AND TOOK ONE.
THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF OVER
HERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT'S AT.
I STOLE EVERYTHING FROM THEM.
IT WAS JUST TOO EASY.
IT'S LIKE I HAD TO GO GET IT.
YOU GUYS ARE CHEATERS.
DIRTY.
CHEATERS.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
HIDDEN IMMUNITY ISLANDS ARE IN
PLAY.
REDEMPTION ISLAND IS NOT.
THAT'S MEANS WHEN YOU ARE VOTED
OUT THIS ACCEPT, THERE IS NO
SECOND CHANCE.
YOU GO HOME.
MEN, HERE'S A MAP TO YOUR NEW
HOME.
WOMEN, MAP TO YOUR NEW HOME.
WE NEED A WOMAN THO 2 HELP US
READ OUR MAP.
Jeff: GUYS YOU'RE HEADING
OUT THAT WAY.
WOMEN YOU'RE HEADING OUT THIS
WAY.
WE'RE NOT LISTENING THOSE
MUSCLES DISURNG US AT ALL.
LET'S LODE UP THE STUFF,
GUYS.
GIRLS IF WE ALL KEEP OUR HEAD
IN THE GAME AND TRY TO STAY
TOGETHER AND TAKE THE BOYS DOWN,
THEN WE'LL BE ONE HUGE BALL OF
BAD-ASSNESS.
AS WE WALKED THROUGH THE
JUNGLE, WE BEGAN TO REALIZE, OH,
MY GOD.
THIS ENCAMPMENT IS HUNDREDS OF
MILES AWAY, AND WE HAD TONS OF
STUFF TO CARRY.
IT WAS A HUGE BURDEN.
WE EACH LOST 10 POUNDS OF WATER
WEIGHT.
I'M TRYING TO ACT ALL TOUGH
BUT INSIDE I'M JUST HURTING,
JUST SUCKING WIND.
BUT THE GUY THAT IMPRESSED ME
THE MOST ON THAT TREK WAS LEIF.
HE WAS CARRYING THE HEAVIEST
THING OUT OF ANYBODY.
YOU KNOW, HE'S A BUFF LITTLE
DUDE.
GOOD?
YEAH.
BACK THERE.
WATCH OUT.
WE'RE STUCK ON SOMETHING.
THIS IS HARDER THAN IT LOOKS.
OH, MY GOD!
PUT THE COCONUT INTO THE
BASKET.
COME ON.
WE CAN DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU SURE?
WELL, THEN PUT THE POT.
GIVE HER THE POT.
YEAH, I WASN'T TOO THRILLED
ABOUT THE MEN VERSUS WOMEN
THING.
I'M A GIRL.
I KNOW, I'M CRAZY.
WE'RE ALL CRAZY.
I MEAN, WOMEN-- AND THAT'S THE
THING TOO, BUT NOE OFFENSE, BUT
WOMEN CAN BE SEE WARM AND THEY
SEEM SO UNDERSTANDING AND
COMPASSIONATE AND ACCEPTING, AND
THEN BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, JUST
LIKE-- YOU KNOW.
YOU BETTER PUT THAT ON YOUR
SHOULDER.
THE HIKE INTO CAMP DEFINITELY
SHOWED WHO ARE THE STRONGER
GIRLS, AND IT'S KIM, MYSELF, AND
CHELSEA.
AND I WOULD SAY SABRINA.
I LOVE KITTY KAT.
SHE WAS A LITTLE WEAK AND SHE
WAS IRRITATING ME, BUT SHE KNEW
THAT.
RIGHT AWAY I ALREADY KNEW WHO
OUR FIVE WAS GOING TO BE AND IT
WAS DONE IN A MATTER OF SECONDS.
IT'S ME YOU, KAT.
SAB.
AND KIM.
I THINK THAT CORE CAN WIN
CHALLENGES, ACTUALLY.
OH, YEAH.
HOW YOU FEELING?
PRETTY GOOD.
I'M HANGING IN THERE.
SIT DOWN, YEAH.
WE'RE GOOD.
WE ALL LOOK ATHLETIC.
WE SEEM PRETTY BRIGHT.
TIME WILL TELL.
IN, RIGHT?
I DIDN'T PLAN TO FORM AN
ALLIANCE RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
I WAS JUST GOING TO LAY LOW BUT
I THINK WHEN THE GUYS STARTED
STEALING OFF THE TRUCK, THAT WAS
A HUGE RIVALRY RIGHT OFF THE
BAT.
AND WHEN THE GUYS DID THAT, THE
GIRLS UPON LIKE, WOMEN POWER!
AND I'M NOT A BIG FAN OF BUT I'M
GOING WITH IT.
LADIES, WE ARE SO CLOSE.
LOOK AT THE MOUNTAINS AND THE
CLOUD.
CRAZY!
THIS IS MANONO!
OKAY, SO WE ALL CAMP TOGETHER.
SO THE GUYS CAMP IS HERE,
TOO.
SO WE'RE ALL TOGETHER.
SHUT UP!
I SWEAR TO GOD-- NO WE'RE
NOT.
WHATEVER.
WHEN WE WALKED ON TO THE
BEACH, WE LOOKED UP AND SAW OUR
FLAG AND WE WERE SO HAPPY TO GET
HERE AND WE LOOKED FIVE TREAT TO
THE RIGHT AND SAW THE MANONO
TRIBE.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
ARE THOSE SUCKERS LIVING US?
I'M LIKE WAIT A MINUTE!
HEY, IT'S GOING TO BE A
PARTY!
WE WERE KIND OF PISSED.
NICE TO SEE YOU, LADIES.
SO WE ACTUALLY DO GET TO SEE
THEM AT LEAST.
WHEN WE SAW OUR FLAG I WAS
EXCITED.
BUT WHEN I SAW THER FLAG NEXT TO
OUR FLAG I WAS JUST CONFUSED.
I WAS LIKE, WAIT.
WHAT?
SO I'M GOING TO HOLD ON TO THIS
JUST IN CASE THE LADIES GET ANY
IDEAS.
WELL, OBVIOUSLY, WE'RE
TOGETHER.
I MEAN, "ONE WORLD."
WELL, IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
ONE WORLD TO ME, BRO.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEIR WORLD AND
OUR WORLD.
DO YOU SEE IT?
THERE'S THREE OF THEM!
THERE'S FOUR.
SHHH!
BE QUIET, BE QUIET.
SO Y'ALL GET ONE AND WE'LL
GET ONE.
ALL RIGHT.
ARE Y'ALL DOWN ON THAT?
WE'LL STRATEGIZE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S ALL WORK
TOGETHER AND WE'LL SPLIT THE
CHICKENS.
THERE'S ONE.
WHERE'S THE OTHER ONE?
ONE'S GOING RIGHT THERE.
HEY, HEY.
YOU BETTER NOT TOUCH OUR
CHICKEN.
GET IT!
ALICIA, GET THE CHICKEN!
LET ME TALK WITH THE GIRLS.
OH, MAN!
WE NEED A SHELTER BUILT.
CHELS, YOU AND I BOTH MADE A
DEAL.
LOOK, IF WE'RE ALL GOING TO LIVE
IN THE SAME AREA, WE HAVE TO
WORK TOGETHER.
LET ME FIGURE OUT WHAT WE
DON'T HAVE THEN WE'LL BARGAIN.
IF I HAD TO DO THE JUMPING ON
THE TRUCK 60-SECOND GRAB ALL
OVER AGAIN I WOULD HAVE STOLE
SOME THINGS THEY STOLE FROM US.
THEY PLAYED DIRTO THAT TRUCK.
WE HAVE A GOOD INCLINING A OF
HOW THEY'RE GOING TO PLAY THE
GAME, AND GAME ON.
WE WILL GIVE THEM THE CHICKEN
BUT WE NEED THEM TO HELP US WITH
OUR SHELTER.
LET'S GO OVER HERE.
I'M NOT A LADIES' MAN.
I'M NOT A GUY THAT'S GOING TO GO
AROUND AND KEEP THE GIRLS HAPPY.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THOSE GIRLS.
GIVE US THAT CHICKEN AS AN
APOLOGY, AND THEN WE'LL THINK
ABOUT TALKING.
SCREW THE CHICKENS FOR NOW.
WE NEED TO BUILD A SHELTER.
THEY NEED US MORE THAN WE
NEED THEM.
AND IT WAS OBVIOUS FROM THAT
MINUTE THAT I'M WITH THE GUYS,
NOT THESE GIRLS.
AND IF YOU CROSS ME, I DON'T
CARE WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE OR WHAT
SEX ARE YOU, I'M NOT WORKING
WITH YOU.
SHE'LL COME TO HER SENSES WHEN
SHE QUITS TRYING TO BE A HERO
AND SHE'LL COME GIVE US A
CHICKEN.
LUMBERJACKS COMING THROUGH.
THERE'S A CLEAR DIVIDE
WITHIN, LIKE, THIS "ONE WORLD."
THERE'S THE GUYS OVER HERE AND
THERE'S THE GIRLS OVER THERE.
I MEAN, I DEFINITELY WANT TO BE
OVER THERE.
WE LOVE YOU.
WE ADORE YOU.
OKAY MY NEW NAME FOR YOU IS
COUNTRY CLUB COCOA.
COUNTRY CLUB COLTON.
HI!
OH, MY GOD!
HOW ARE YOU?
I MEAN, THE MINUTE I SAW
COLTON I KNEW COLTON WAS GAY.
HE'S VERY COMFORTABLE WITH IT.
GOOD FOR HIM.
COUNTRYGIRL, WHAT'S YOUR
NAME, CHELSEA?
I'M COLTON.
HI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I LOVE YOU ALREADY.
I ALSO KNEW THAT HE WAS GOING
TO HAVE PROBLEMS IDENTIFYING
WITH THE GUYS AROUND CAMP.
THERE'S A LOT OF MANLY MEN
AROUND HERE.
NOBODY HAS AN ISSUE WITH HIM
BEING GAY OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST HE DOESN'T TRY TO FIT
IN AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, THE FIRST CHANCE I
HAVE, GIRL POWER.
I'M GOING TO BE OVER HERE.
IF COLTON DOESN'T FIX, THAT
HE'S GOING TO BE GOING HOME
QUICK.
I MEAN, I JUST KNOW,
IMMEDIATELY, I'M-- WE'RE LIVING
WITH THE GIRLS.
THE GIRLS ARE GOING TO LIKE ME.
IF YOU GET-- IF YOU'RE MORE
ONE OF THE GIRLS THAN ONE OF THE
GUYS THEY'RE ALL GOING TO WANT
TO GET RID OF YOU.
IF YOU'RE ONE OF THE GUYS AND
WANT TO BE A RUNNER AND USE THAT
TO OUR ADVANTAGE, THE ACCESS,
YOU'RE SAFE.
SO DO THAT AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
ALL RIGHT?
MATT IS-- HE'S VERY ARROGANT,
FIRST OFF.
HE'S VERY CONDESCENDING AND HE
THINKS HE'S RUNNING THIS SHOW.
BUT IF I GET WHAT I WANT, HIS
TORCH IS GOING OUT.
SO IS THIS THE FRATTED BOY
ALLIANCE OVER HERE?
YEAH.
YOU GUYS ARE WORKING HARD.
FRAT BOYS?
I WAS BLINDED BY THE HOTNESS,
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE PUTTING A HUGE TARGET
ON OUR BACK.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
WHAT IS ANYBODY GOING TO DO
ABOUT THAT?
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
YOU GET FOUR STRONG.
THE WAY "SURVIVOR" WORKS IS THE
STRONG SAY BECAUSE THEY BENEFIT
THE TRIBE AND THE WEAK GO.
I'M ALIGNED WITH BIG MIKE,
J-BIRD AND BILL.
IT'S AN EASY ALLIANCE.
WE'RE THE YOUNG, FIT GUYS.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET
ANY "SURVIVOR" POINT FOR THAT
ONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT MORE WE
NEED TO TALK ABOUT.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS SCREWED.
( LAUGHS )
I'M IN THE GROUP AND I'M
HAPPY AND IT'S THE DOMINANT
ALLIANCE, CLEARLY, SO I'M SIT,
PRETTY, AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
WHERE ARE MY MATCHES?
CAN I-- HOLD ON.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
YEAH.
CAN I TALK TO YOU THREE JUST
FAIR SECOND?
SURE.
I AM NOT, LIKE, TRYING TO BE
"THAT PERSON" BUT IF ANY OF YOU
FIND, LIKE A CLUE TO AN IDOL OR
ANYTHING, LIKE, YOU KNOW WHO
NEEDS IT THE MOST.
'CAUSE THERE'S ONLY TWO THINGS
THAT ARE GOING TO KEEP ME THIS
GAME AND IT'S THE IDOL AND JESUS
AND HE AIN'T SHOWING UP.
COLTON IS A WILD CARD.
I-- MY GUT ITS TELLING ME TO
BELIEVE IN HIM, BUT WHO KNOWS?
ANYTHING CAN GO DOWN IN
"SURVIVOR" BUT HE HAS ME
CRACKING UP IN STITCHES.
AND IF HUMOR IS HIS ARMOR, THEN
HE HAS ALL OF US SOLD LIKE
SUCKERS, SO I LIKE HIM.
EVEN THOUGH THIS IS ONE
WORLD, TWO ME IT'S TWO
HEMISPHERES
THEIR TRIBE VERSUS OUR
TRIBE.
I DON'T REALLY THINK THE WOMEN'S
TRIBES WANTS TO BE IN WITH US.
THEY'RE KEEPING EVERYTHING ON
THEIR SIDE SO I DON'T WANT TO
HELP THEM IN ANY WAY POSSIBLE.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED, THEY
NEED TO STAY ON THEIR SIDE.
I'LL STAY ON MINE.
AND IF THEY NEED US MORE THAN WE
NEED THEM, THEN WE'RE IN CHARGE
OF THIS GAME.
COME ON, BABY, LIGHT.
YEAH, BABY.
THAT'S IT.
GOT IT.
SWEET!
WHAT'S UP?
I'M SABRINA.
WHAT'S UP, SABRINA.
WE-- WE GOT OUR FIRE STARTED.
I SEE!
AND-- AND--
WHO GOT THE FIRE GOING?
YOU GUYS ARE LOOKING AT ME LIKE
I'M KRYPTONITE OR SOMETHING.
JUST LET ME PUT IT OUT THERE.
WOULD YOU BE INTERESTED IF WE
SWAPPED-- IF SOMEONE CAME OVER
AND STARTED A FIRE, AND WE GAVE
YOU A CHICKEN?
WE SAID WE'D WORK TOGETHER
AND SPLIT THE CHICKEN, NO MATTER
WHO CAUGHT THEM.
OKAY, WE'LL SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
THE WOMEN DEFINITELY NOTICED
THE FIRE, AND AS SOON AS THEY
SAW THAT SMOKE, THEY CAME
A-RUNNIN''.
I'M JUST CHECKING IT OUT.
I'M JUST CHICKING IT OUT.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
WHERE IS THAT CHICKEN?
I AM THE MASTER OF THE
CHICKEN.
THE CHICKEN THING SET THINGS
OFF ON THE WRONG NOTE.
THEY WANT US TO GIVE THEM FIRE
AND THAT AIN'T GOING TO HAPPEN.
SINCE YOU GUYS STOLE OUR AXE,
MAYBE WE COULD TRADE THAT AWX
STOLE.
LISTEN, YOU HAVE NINE GUYS
HERE WHO ARE LOOKING FOR A
CHICKEN AND THEY'RE NEGOTIATING.
YOU GIRLS ALWAYS COME BARE
HANDED.
YEAH.
LISTEN, WE'RE BEYOND THE
CHARM.
YOU'RE BEYOND THE CHARM?
LISTEN, I'M A LITTLE TOO OLD FOR
CHARM.
WHAT ARE YOU KIDDING ME!
THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK!
IT WAS WORTH A TRY.
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU,
THESE CHICKS OVER THERE, THEY'RE
IN KOOKUE-LAND.
THEY WANT TO TRADE FIRE FAIR
CHICKEN.
IT'S THE FIRST DAYS, IT'S THE
FIRST HOURS.
WE DON'T NEED A CHICKEN.
IF MONICA TAKES HER PANTS OFF
WILL YOU GET US ONE.
MONICA, WE'RE GOING TO SET UP
A POLE AND YOU GIRLS USE THE
GIRL AND WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW NAKED.
IF WE GET NAKED, WE GET WHAT?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
WE HAVE NO CONTROL OVER THAT.
SEE, THEY'RE NOT AGREEING TO
ANYTHING.
THE GIRLS ARE SO TYPICAL.
I'VE BEEN AROUND 50 YEARS, LADY.
YOU DIDN'T JUST COME OVER HERE
WITH A SET OF TATTERS ON YOU AND
WALKING AROUND IN YOUR BIKINI.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING FIRE FROM ME
IN THE FIRST DAY.
YOU HAVE TO SUFFER TWO OR THREE
DAYS AND MAYBE ONE BY ONE
THEY'LL QUIT-- "WE'RE DONE!
THIS IS NOT WHAT I SIGNED UP
FOR."
LET'S GO RINSE OFF.
AND THINK ABOUT THE FIRE WE
DON'T HAVE.
I JUST WISH WE HAD A LITTLE
BIT OF FIRE SO WE COULD HANG OUT
AND TALK.
WAIT, MAYBE WE SHOULD GO OVER
TO THE GUYS' CAMP AND JUST ASK
IF THEY MIGHT WANT TO GIVE US
FIRE.
IT'S NOT JUST THEY WANT FIRE.
I WANT TO SEE YOU GUYS.
I WANT TO TALK MORE.
I WANT A CAMPFIRE SETTING.
IT'S ALL ABOUT THE AMBIANCE.
ME, TOO, ME, TOO-- WHAT DOES
THAT MEAN, AMBIANCE?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN.
WE WERE JUST GOING IT COME
AND SEE IF YOU WANTED TO GIVE US
FIRE NOW.
DO YOU WANT TO SHARE AT ALL.
WE JUST WANT TO SEE EACH
OTHER SO WE CAN TALK.
REALLY.
WE WANT CAMPFIRE SETTING.
I DON'T KNOW IF FIRE IS GOING
TO HAPPEN.
WHO DO WE HAVE TO CONVINCE?
WHO DO YOU THINK IS RUNG THE
SHOW OVER HERE?
TARZAN?
YOU THINK TARZAN IS RUNNING
THE SHOW THE OVER HERE.
AOOOHHHH!
YOU SEE TARZAN AND THINK HE
MUST BE CALLING THE SHOTS.
I'M JUST ASKING.
MATT, AND BILL AND YOU.
THEY'RE DEHYDRATED.
THERE'S NO WATER.
THEY CAN'T BOIL THE FIRE SO US
HAVING FIRE IS A BIG ADVANTAGE.
IS THAT A NO, JAY?
IS THAT A NO?
YOU'RE AT WAR HERE, PERIOD.
SOMEBODY HAS TO BEAT SOMEBODY,
SO I THINK ANY DEAL WITH THE
GIRLS AT THIS POINT IS
LUDICROUS.
THEY'RE DOWN.
KEEP THEM DOWN.
IF THEY GET FIRE ON THEIR OWN,
GOOD FOR THEM.
IF THEY DON'T, LET THEM
STRUGGLE.
( SNORING )
TONIGHT, CHRISTINA AND I
THOUGHT THE BOYS STOLE THE AXE
FROM US, SO LET'S GO OVER AND
STEAL AN EMBER FROM THEM.
SHOOT.
I MEAN, WE'RE HERE.
MIGHT AS WELL JUST DO IT.
OKAY, LET'S GIVE IT A WHIRL.
DO YOU GUYS WANT PINEAPPLE
FOR BREAKFAST BECAUSE THAT'S ALL
WE'VE GOT?
YEAH, MAYBE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE Y'ALL STOLE A
FIRE IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
YEAH.
LAST NIGHT WE WENT OVER AND
TRIED TO STEAL AN EMBER.
DID WE START A FIRE?
YEAH.
DID IT LAST?
NO, IT DIED.
COME ON.
I SMELL IT.
DO YOU SMELL IT?
YOU CAN'T SMELL THAT?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME!
I SMELL WOOD BURNING.
FIRE IS SO IMPORTANT.
WE NEED TO GET THAT FIRE TO-DAY.
OH, GOD.
I CAN'T DO THAT FAST BY MYSELF.
I THINK SOME OF THESE GIRLS
WHO HAVE THIS CHIP ON THEIR
SHOULDER THINKING WE DON'T NEED
THE GUYS.
LOOK, IT'S NOT SO MUCH ABOUT
PRIDE IT'S ABOUT, YES, WE HAVE A
GAME TO PLAY, BUT WE ALSO NEED
TO SURVIVE AS WELL.
LOOK, GUYS, WE REALLY NEED
FIRE.
WHAT IS IT GOING TO TAKE THAT WE
CAN WORK TOGETHER, LIKE, FOR
FIRE, FOR INSTANCE?
IF YOU GUYS ARE WILLING TO
LEAVE US 40 OF THOSE--
YEAH, WE WILL--
WE WOULD GIVE YOU FIRE, AND
WE WOULD EVEN MAKE IT FOR YOU.
40?
IT'S JUST-- THAT'S SO MUCH.
THAT'S A LOT OF WORK.
20, EACH PERSON DO TWO?
20 FRONDS AND YOU'VE GOT A
DEAL.
OKAY.
SHE IS A NEGOTIATOR.
I'VE LEARNED A LOT.
CHRISTINA KEEPS GOING TO THE
BOYS' CAMP, MAKING DEALS.
EVERY TIME PEOPLE FIND HER SHE'S
DOING, LIKE, HANDSHAKES AND
THINGS LIEB THAT.
SHE'S TRYING TO MAKE LITTLE
PEACE TREATIES WITH THE GUYS.
I'M NOT STUPID POOP WE CAN DO 20
AND THEY'LL DO FIRE.
BUT WE NEED THEIR FRONDS.
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
DONE.
ARE YOU BRINGING IT TO US OR
DO WE HAVE TO CARRY IT?
WE'LL COME OVER HERE, WE'LL
DO IT--
NO, SHE WANTS THEM BROUGHT TO
HER.
WE WILL WEAVE FOR THEM, BUT
WE ARE GOING TO WEAVE AT OUR
CAMP AND THEY'RE GOING TO BRING
US OUR FIRE.
LET ME TELL THEM.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO WANT TO DO
THEM OVER HERE.
I'M ABOUT TO PUNCH CHRISTINA
THERE HER FACE.
I SEE WHAT SHE'S DOING.
SHE'S TRYING TO BE FRIENDLY WITH
THE GUYS AND SHE'S GOING TO BE
THE FIRST ONE TO GO, FIRST ONE
TO GO.
I JUST WENT TO GO KIND OF,
YOU KNOW, TAKE A BATH, AND ON MY
WAY BACK I SAID, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET ME LOOK FOR THE IDOL WHERE
ARE YOU?
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY.
I AM HAVING AN AMAZING DAY.
LITERALLY, THE SECOND PLACE I
LOOKED, I'M LIKE, "OH, MY GOD!
THERE'S A PACKAGE."
I FOUND THE IDOL!
OH, MY GOD.
ANOTHER ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
FOR THE MANONO TRIBE.
IF YOU'RE NOT A MANONO TRIBE
MEMBER YOU MUST GIVE THIS TO
SOMEONE.
I FOUND AN IDOL BUT IT'S NOT FOR
ME.
THE RULE SAYS IT'S FOR THE
MANONO TRIBE.
I HAVE TO GIVE IT UP BEFORE THE
NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND I'M
JUST TRYING TO THINK, LIKE, WHO
SHOULD I GIVE IT TO?
THANK YOU, GUYS.
OUR MAIN THING SGIRLS, I
DON'T WANT TO CAUSE SOMETHING IN
YOUR ALL CAMP, BUT I NEED A
PARTNER TO HELP ME FIND AN IDOL.
I HAVE TO SAVE SOMEONE FROM
THE GUYS' TEAM.
THAT COULD HURT OR HELP ME.
COLTON IS THE OBVIOUS CHOICE.
I FOUND AN IDOL BUT IT'S NOT
FOR ME.
I CAN'T USE IT FOR ANYONE ON MY
TEAM.
I HAVE TO GIVE IT TO ONE OF YOU
GUYS.
I HAVE TO SAVE YOU.
OBVIOUSLY, I'M HER
FIRST-CHOICE CANDIDATE TO GIVE
THE IDOL TO.
IT'S TAKE, EVERYTHING NOT TO
JUMP UP AND DOWN RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS, LIKE, MY SAVING GRACE.
COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
YES.
WHOOO!
Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
ON MY GO, ONE AT A TIME YOU WILL
JUMP FROM A 25-FOOT TOWER INTO A
NET BELOW.
YOU'LL THEN RACE ACROSS A GIANT
BALANCE BEAM AND MAKE YOUR WAY
OVER A LONG ROPE BRIDGE.
ONCE ALL YOUR TRIBE MEMBERS ARE
AT THE MAT, RAISE YOUR TRIBE
FLAG.
FIRST TRIBE TO RELEASE THEIR
FLAG WINS IMMUNITY AND IS SAFE
FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
ONE WORLD" AND SENT HOME.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
BIG STAKES.
WORTH PLAYING FOR.
YES.
OH, YEAH!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
THIS IS A VERY HIGH FALL.
MAKE SURE YOU KEEP YOUR ARMS TO
YOUR CHEST AND LAND ON YOUR
BACK.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD IN THE
FORM OF FIRE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BILL JUMPS, KAT JUMPS.
BILL LOSES A SHOE ON THE MAT.
GOTTA GET TO THE MAT BEFORE THE
NEXT PERSON CAN GO
GO MEN!
GO, WOMEN!
JONAS DROPS.
SABRINA LANDED FEET FIRST.
LAND ON YOUR BACK!
GUYS HAVE A BIT OF A LEAD.
LET'S GO, NINA!
Jeff: NINA WITH A FACE
PLANT.
TROYZAHN MAKES IT.
HERE GOES LEIF.
KOURTNEY GIVES IT A GO.
KOURTNEY FALLS HARD ON HER
HANDS.
KEEP YOUR HANDS ON YOUR CHEST.
NOW, NOW, NOW!
GO, GO, GO!
GO, KOURTNEY, GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: KOURTNEY IS REALLY
NURSING THAT HAND.
COME OKOURTNEY.
MY WRIST.
Jeff: HERE COMES ALICIA.
GO, TORZAHN!
Jeff: HERE COMES COLTON.
COLTON LANDS HARD.
FEET FIRST.
MONICA, THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT!
YEAH, THAT'S IT, THAT'S IT.
YOU GOT IT, YOU GOT IT!
Jeff: MATT GRABS THE SHOE,
JAY, THE LAST GUY TO GO.
GUYS HAVE A ONE-PERSON LEAD
RIGHT NOW.
COME ON, COME ON!
Jeff: THE MEN CAN MOVE ON
NOW.
GO, MEN!
YOU GOT IT, YOU GOT IT, YOU
GOT IT!
Jeff: THE MEN ARE ALREADY
ON TO THE BALANCE BEAM.
THE WOMEN ARE BEHIND, NEED TO
PICK UP SOME TIME.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON, COME ON!
Jeff: JONAS WITH A NICE
SAVE.
KAT CATCHING UP.
JONAS AND CATARE ACROSS.
KOURTNEY WITH A SERIOUS INJURY
HOLDING THAT WRIST.
TROYZAHN GIVING IT A GO.
SABRINA FALLS OFF.
THE MEN HAVE A TWO-PERSON LEAD.
IT'S A LONG CHALLENGE.
COME ON.
KOURTNEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
UHM, I'M REALLY DIZZY, I'M
REALLY DIZZY.
I DON'T THINK I CAN DO IT.
Jeff: EVERYBODY HOLD UP!
STOP WHERE YOU'RE AT!
STOP!
MEDICAL.
WE NEED MEDICAL IN TO SEE
KOURTNEY.
LET ME SUPPORT IT.
DON'T LET ME MOVE IT.
ANY PAIN HERE?
YES, YES.
CAN YOU MOVE THAT THUMB?
NO.
CAN YOU WIGGLE YOUR FINGERS
AT ALL?
CAN YOU MAKE A FIST?
CAN YOU BEND IT BACK AT ALL?
THAT HURTS.
ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: RAMONA GIVE US AN
UPDATE.
WHEN KOURTNEY CAME OFF THE
NET HE LANDED WITH HER ARM DOWN
LIKE THAT ON THE SO SHE BENT IT
BACK AND IT LOOKS LIKE THE BONE
MIGHT BE BROKEN HERE.
YOU CAN SEE A BIG BEND THERE.
SOMETIMES WHEN YOU JUST SPRAIN
SOMETHING IT CAN BRUISE AND IT
CAN SWELL UP, SO I WANT TO MAKE
SURE IT IS NOT JUST A BAD SPRAIN
THAT IT ISN'T BROKEN.
WE'D LIKE TO GET AN X-RAY TO
ASSESS THAT.
Jeff: SO IT'S UNCLEAR RIGHT
NOW WHAT IT IS FOR SURE.
UH-HUH.
Jeff: NULL X-RAY, YOU WON'T
KNOW.
YUP.
Jeff: WHICH MEANS WE'RE NOT
SURE OF HER STATUS IN THE GAME
AT THIS POINT.
ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: OKAY.
SO WHY DON'T YOU TAKE HER OUT OF
HERE, DO A QUICK X-RAY.
WE WILL GET BACK TOGETHER IN THE
AFTERNOON AND FIGURE OUT THE
STATUS OF THAT.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
( APPLAUSE )
OKAY.
Jeff: SO HERE'S THE UPDATE.
WE'RE GOING TO GET KOURTNEY AN
X-RAY, SEE HER STATUS IN THE
GAME.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S UNCLEAR.
TECHNICALLY, THIS CHALLENGE
REQUIRES NINE PEOPLE START, NINE
PEOPLE FINISH.
SO BY THE RULES, THIS CHALLENGE
IS OVER.
THE MEN HAVE WON AND THEY CAN
TAKE THE VICTORY RIGHT NOW AND
SEND THE WOMEN TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
NOW, BECAUSE IT IS ONLY DAY
THREE IN A 39-DAY GAME, THE MEN,
IF YOU WANT, CAN MAKE A GESTURE
OF GOOD WILL, AND SAY LET'S
FINISH THIS CHALLENGE.
IF YOU FOUR WANT TO JOIN THESE
FIVE AND HASH IT OUT REAL QUICK,
DO IT.
YEAH, DUDE.
Jeff: THE ONLY THING I'M
REMINDING YOU GUYS OF IS THAT IT
IS THE SINGLE BIGGEST MISTAKE
MADE IN THIS GAME IS DOING
DECISIONS EARLY ON THAT NOBODY
WILL FORGIVE YOU FOR IN THE END,
BUT IT IS YOUR CALL.
DO YOU WANT TO VOTE?
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WHAT'S THE DECISION?
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE IMMUNITY.
Jeff: MEANING YOU'RE GOING
TO WIN THE CHALLENGE RIGHT NOW.
YEAH.
WE REALLY THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO GO THE OPPOSITE WAY.
COME OGUYS!
DON'T YOU WANT TO FINISH THE
GAME?
DON'T YOU GUYS WANT TO FINISH
AND COMPLETE IT AND DO IT THE
RIGHT WAY?
I UNDERSTAND.
IF IT WAS REVERSED AND ONE OF US
GOT HURT, I JUST DON'T THINK IT
WOULD BE THE SAME THING.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
LET ME JUST FINISH, LET ME
JUST TALK.
THE OBJECT OF THIS GAME IS TO
WIN.
OKAY?
THERE'S PLENTY OF CHALLENGES
LEFT IF YOU GUYS WANT TO PROVE
YOURSELF THAT YOU CAN DO IT, BUT
THERE'S NO WAY YOU GUYS WOULD
SAY, "LET'S PLAY OVMENT.
YOU JUST WOULDN'T DO IT.
I JUST DON'T BUY IT.
LET'S GO!
BRING IT ON!
WE WON.
Jeff: THE CHALLENGE IS
OVER?
YEAH.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MEN, NO
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
WOMEN, I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL AND I WILL GIVE YOU AN
UPDATE ON KOURTNEY.
IN OUR MINDS, WE KNEW THAT
THERE WAS NO CHANCE THEY WOULD
JUST TAKE THE IMMUNITY, AND WHEN
THEY DID, IT WAS, LIKE,
HEARTBREAK.
THOSE GUYS DON'T GIVE A CRAP
ABOUT ANY OF US GIRLS AND THEY
SHOWED IT TODAY.
THEY DON'T CARE.
THIS IS A NO-MERCY GAME.
YEAH, THE CHALLENGE.
WOW.
WHAT A DISAPPOINTMENT.
I FEEL SO BAD FOR KOURTNEY, AND
I HOPE SHE'S OKAY, BUT IT'S
DISAPPOINTING NOT TO BE ABLE TO
FINISH IT AND ONLY GOT THROUGH
THE FIRST PART OF IT, AND THIS
IS WHAT HAPPENED.
( LAUGHS )
I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS HAPPENED!
YEAH, IT SUCKED THAT WE
COULDN'T, YOU KNOW--
I KNOW, I WANTED TO AT LEAST
TRY IT.
IT'S KIND OF, LIKE, WHAT HAD
TO BE DONE.
MY ONLY THING IS I FELT LIKE WE
WERE GOING TO BEAT YOU GUYS
ANYWAY.
I GUESS WE'LL NEVER KNOW.
NEVER KNOW NOW.
IT'S A GAME, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE GUYS WITH THE NOT WANTING
TO FINISH THE CHALLENGE, YOU
KNOW, I GET IT.
IN HINDSIGHT I CAN LOOK BACK AND
SEE MAYBE WHAT THEY WERE
THINKING.
BUT I'M FROM TEXAS, MEN ARE
CHIVALROUS, GREW UP WATCHING
WESTERNS.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, NO GUY I KNOW
WOULD HAVE MADE THAT CHOICE.
RIGHT NOW, IT LOOKS LIKE WHO
HAS MAJORITY OF THE NUMBERS?
HOW IS IT SPLIT UP?
4-4 WITH ME IN THE MIDDLE.
IF YOU SAY IT'S 4-4, YOU'RE
THE SWING VOTE, RIGHT?
THAT'S YOUR BIG MOMENT IN THIS
GAME TO KNOCK OUT ONE OF THE BIG
GUYS.
BECAUSE THE THING STHAT THE
STRONG GUYS ARE ONLY KEEPING YOU
ON BECAUSE THEY KNOW YOU'RE
DISPOSABLE.
NO, THEY'RE KEEPING ME
BECAUSE THEY WANT ME TO BE ABLE
TO WORK Y'ALL.
RIGHT, YOU'RE DISPOSABLE
THEY'RE GOING TO PLAY YOU.
BUT WHEN I GET WITH YOU ALL--
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
SO I'M GIVING YOU THIS IDOL.
I LOVE YOU.
LISTEN, LISTEN VERY
CAREFULLY.
I MEAN RIGHT NOW IT'S UP TO YOU
HOW YOU PLAY IT.
THIS IS THE BIG MOVE THAT
EVERYBODY IS LOOKING FOR.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE THE RISK.
FORGET WHO'S GOING TO BE PISSED
OFF AT YOU.
SWING OVER AND THINK ABOUT THE
GAY GUY THAT COME INSIDE WHO
EVERYBODY THINKS IS GOING TO GET
OUT IN THE FIRST ROUND, YOU COME
OVER AND YOU KNOCK OFF ONE OF
THE BIGGEST PEOPLE THERE.
HE HEADS INTO THE MERGE AND
THEN WE'RE GOING TO TURN THIS
AROUND.
DON'T LET HIM PUNK YOUR ASS,
ALL RIGHT?
I WANT YOU TO STAY AROUND, OKAY.
THIS ISLAND WOULD NOT BE FUN
WITHOUT YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
LOVE YOU MORE.
MATT THINKS I'M A PUPPET AND
HE'S IN FOR A HUGE SURPRISE IF
EVERYTHING GOES LIKE I WANT IT
TO.
WE'RE GOING TO CUT HIS THROAT
FASTER THAN TAYLOR SWIFT WILL
WRITE A SONG ABOUT HER NEXT
BOYFRIEND.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THE BIG
ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM?
WE DON'T WANT TO WAIT UNTIL THE
LAST MINUTE BECAUSE WE ARE GOING
TO TRIBAL TONIGHT, TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
I DON'T KNOW IF SHE'S OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
EVEN IF SHE'S BACK IN THE GAME,
HOW CAN SHE REALLY PARTICIPATE?
REALLY?
I MEAN--
SHE BROKE HER WRIST.
SHE SAID SHE HEARD IT CRACK.
I GUESS WE JUST WAIT AND SEE.
HARD TO DECIDE WITHOUT
HEARING.
I HOPE-- THIS IS GOING TO
SOUND MEAN-- BUT HOPEFULLY SHE'S
GETTING X-RAYED AND JUST REALLY
GETTING USED TO THE AIR
CONDITIONING THERE, AND GETTING
A FRESH DRINK OF WATER AND
SAYING, "I LIKE THIS," AND DON'T
COME BACK.
KOURTNEY, POOR KOURTNEY.
SO UNCOORDINATED.
OBVIOUSLY, SHE BROKE HER WRIST.
BUT I'M GOING TO DEFINITELY TURN
THE TABLES AROUND AND LET THEM
KNOW THAT CHRISTINA NEEDS TO GO.
IT'S GUYS VERSUS GIRLS, AND
SHE'S PLAYING THAT SIDE AND
PLAYING US AT THE SAME TIME.
SHE'S POISON.
SO I'M GOING TO CALL HER OUT.
I ALREADY KNOW IT.
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO SEE
WHEN WE GET THERE WHO IS GOING
TO BE KICKED OUT.
Jeff: BEHIND IECH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH.
APPROACH A FLAME, DIP IT IN, AND
GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
WELL, WELCOME TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN UPDATE ON
KOURTNEY'S CONDITION IN A FEW
MINUTES.
FIRST I WANT TO GET A LAY OF THE
LAND OF THE FIRST TWO DAYS.
ALICIA ATELL ME ABOUT THE FIRST
MOMENT WHEN YOU WALK ON TO YOUR
CAMP AND YOU REALIZE, WE'RE
GOING TO BE LIVING WITH THE MEN?
I ACTUALLY LIKE TO BOND WITH
GIRLS BETTER.
MY WEAKNESS WOULD HAVE BEEN THE
GUYS BEING, LIKE, WITH US SO I'M
GLAD THAT THEY MOVED OUT.
Jeff: KAT, WHO IS LEADING
THIS TRIBE?
EVERYBODY ON THIS TRIBE HAS A
ROLE THAT THEY'RE PLAYING.
LIKE, I CONTROL THE FIRE.
BUT EVERYONE DOES THEIR
INDIVIDUAL ROLES.
Jeff: SO YOU HANDLE FIRE.
AND, KRISTINA, HOW DID YOU GUYS
GET FIRE?
WELL, WE WENT OVER TO THE
GUYS AND I SAID, "LOOK, IS THERE
ANYTHING THAT WE CAN DO THAT WE
CAN WORK WITH WHERE YOU CAN HELP
US WITH THE FIRE BECAUSE WE NEED
IT TODAY."
I CAN INTERRUPT?
WHAT HAPPENED WAS A SHADY DEAL
WENT DOWN.
SHE TOLD THE GUYS SHE WOULD HAVE
TWO GIRLS WEAVE FOR THEM.
I DIDN'T TELL THEM I WOULD
HAVE TWO GIRLS WEAVE FOR THEM.
HOLD IT, I'M TALKING.
COME ON!
YOU DID.
WE COULD HAVE KOURTNEY--
YES, YOU DID.
THANK YOU FOR THE CLARIFICATION.
NOW WE CAN MOVE ON.
HOWEVER, IT DID BENEFIT US.
IT DID BENEFIT US, YES.
WE DID GET FIRE THIS WHOLE TIME.
Jeff: I'M STILL NOT 100%
SURE WHAT HAPPENED.
ALICIA, THE DEAL WAS EXACTLY
WHAT?
THAT WE WOULD HAVE TWO GIRLS
WEAVE IN THEIR CAMP.
NO, THAT WAS NOT TRUE.
SO I WANT TO CLARIFY BECAUSE ALL
THE FACTS HERE ARE COMPLETELY
FALSE, OKAY.
THE GUYS--
THEN WHY DID YOU--
SHH!
BECAUSE YOU'RE WRONG!
OKAY?
SO SHUT UP!
REALLY?
REALLY.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE THE
FACTS RIGHT.
OKAY, I WAS STANDING THERE.
WELL YOU KNOW WHO, IF THIS
GAME IS ALL ABOUT--
STOP, STOP, STOP.
COME ON.
DO YOU WANT TO TELL YOUR SIDE
OR NOT.
WE GOT A FIRE PIT AND A
BETTER PIT THAN WE COULD HAVE
CREATED.
Jeff: CHELSEA, DO YOU GUYS
NEED TO OPERATE FIRST AS A GROUP
OF WOMEN BEFORE ANYBODY GOES
INTO THE ENEMY TERRITORY OR IS
IT, HEY, EVERYBODY IS PLAYING
THEIR OWN INDIVIDUAL GAME, DO
WHAT YOU WANT?
EVERYBODY IS DOING WHAT THEY
WANT.
I THINK EVEN IF WE SAID LET'S
TALK ABOUT EVERY SINGLE THING WE
NEED TO DECIDE ON AS A GROUP, IT
STILL WOULDN'T HAPPEN.
IT'S WOMEN.
WE CAN'T ALL AGREE ON
EVERYTHING, AND THAT'S JUST PART
OF IT.
Jeff: AND, MONICA, IT
DOESN'T APPEAR THAT THERE'S ANY
LEADER.
UN, IT'S ALMOST LIKE WHATEVER
IS RIGHT IN FRONT OF US THAT HAS
TO HAPPEN RIGHT NOW TAKES
PRECEDENT.
IT'S CRAZY.
IT'S TOTALLY ANARCHY.
Jeff: AND YOU'RE LAUGHING
ABOUT IT LIKE IT'S KIND OF
FUNNY.
BUT WHAT'S NOT FUNNY IS COMING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU'VE GOT HUGE ANIMOSITY
BETWEEN AT LEAST TWO PEOPLE.
YOU HAVE NO STRUCTURE.
AND RIGHT NOW, THE GUYS ARE
THINKING THOSE WOMEN ARE ALL
OVER THE MAP.
WE HAVE THEM RIGHT WHERE WE WANT
THEM-- NUTSVILLE.
OKAY.
LET ME GIVE YOU AN UPDATE ON
KOURTNEY.
SOME GOOD NEWS AND SOME BAD
NEWS.
SHE'S DOING FINE.
SHE'S IN GOOD SPIRITS.
BUT HER WRIST IS BROKEN IN A FEW
PLACES.
IT WILL REQUIRE SURGERY.
AND SHE IS OUT OF THE GAME.
THAT'S THE BAD NEWS.
THE GOOD NEWS, NOBODY ELSE IS
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
IN ADDITION, BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU'LL NOW GO
BACK WITH FIRE.
YEAH!
( APPLAUSE )
Jeff: AND AS I SEND YOU ON
YOUR WAY, I'D SAY THERE'S A
LITTLE MORE GOOD NEWS AND A
LITTLE MORE BAD NEWS.
THE OTHER GOOD NEWS SIT'S ONLY
DAY THREE.
PLENTY OF TIME TO TURN THINGS
AROUND.
BAD NEWS, THERE ARE 36 DAYS LEFT
IN THIS GAME, AND IF YOU DON'T
GET IT TOGETHER, NONE OF YOU
WILL MAKE IT TO THE END.
THAT'S WHAT I SEND YOU HOME WITH
TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR: THE WOMEN OF SALANI
GO FROM BAD TO WORSE.
WOMEN COMPLETELY FALLING APART.
RIGHT NOW WE LOOK LIKE
IDIOTS.
Jeff: AND COLTON IS ON AN
ISLAND OF HIS OWN.
COLTON IS THE WORST PERSON
FOR OUR TRIBE.
COLTON IS A VIRUS.
IF YOU WANT TO MESS WITH ME,
BY ALL MEANS, BUT YOU AIN'T
GONNA WIN.
I'M NOT SO PROUD OF MYSELF
RIGHT NOW.
BUT IT KIND OF WASN'T MY FAULT
BUT IT WAS.
I FEEL LIKE IF I HAD MOVED MY
ARM OUT A LITTLE FARTHER I
WOULDN'T BE IN THE SITUATION I
AM RIGHT NOW.
BUT IF MY SON SEES SOMETHING
POSITIVE ABOUT ME FROM THIS
EXPERIENCE I WOULD LIKE TO THINK
HE THINKS I'M A STRONG WOMAN