Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
AFTER THE MERGE, THE FORMER
SALANI MEMBERS SET OUT ON A
PLAN.
ME AND JANE, MIKE, WE HAVE
THIS PACT TO STICK WITH CHELSEA,
KIM, KAT, AND SABRINA.
Jeff: AT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE, A SCHOOLYARD PICK
SPLIT THE TRIBE INTO TWO TEAMS.
LEIF FLIES OFF THAT SLIDE!
KIM'S TEAM WAS VICTORIOUS.
YELLOW TRIBE ENJOYING YOUR
BARBECUE REWARD.
EARNING A REWARD AWAY FROM CAMP
WHILE TROYZAN AND JAY'S TEAM WAS
LEFT EMPTY HANDED.
WITH TROY AND JAY LEFT BEHIND,
KIM AND SABRINA SAW A CHANCE TO
MAKE A NEW PLAN.
IT HAS TO BE ALL GIRLS.
I SAY WE TELL TROY.
MIKE IS TRYING TO GET YOU OUT OF
HERE.
WE CAN START A REVOLUTION AND
GET RID OF MIKE AND APHI LATE
THEM.
Jeff: AFTER THE REWARD, KIM
WASTED LITTLE TIME PUTTING THE
PLAN INTO MOTION.
I WON'T BE SURPRISED IF THEY
MAKE THE MOVE.
Jeff: JAY BECAME
SUSPICIOUS.
I'M SCARED OF Y'ALL GIRLS.
Y'ALL GET RID OF HIM; Y'ALL GET
RID OF ME NEXT.
I DON'T TRUST THE GIRLS.
THERE'S TOO MANY GIRLS THAT
COULD HOOK UP AND START KNOCKING
OUT ALL THESE GUYS.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
KIM'S BOLD MOVE PAID OFF.
EIGHTH PERSON PAID OFF AND THE
SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY, MIKE.
MIKE JOINED JONAS AS THE SECOND
MAN ON THE JOURNEY.
CAN THE MEN RECOVER FROM THEIR
NUMBERS DISADVANTAGE OR WILL THE
WOMEN TAKE OVER THE GAME?
TEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
NO WAY!
THAT'S CRAZY.
WE HAVE A FEW GUYS LEFT AND
THEY HAVE THE VOTE CHALLENGE.
THEY NEED TO SET THE GAME, WE'RE
GOING TO LOSE.
I DON'T MEAN...
LISTEN, I'M JUST PLAGUE OUT,
THOSE GIRLS ARE PLOTTING TO
KNOCK US ALL OUT ONE BY ONE AND
THEY'RE DOING IT AND IT'S
BECAUSE WE FELL APART.
NO, I KNOW.
BUT MIKE WAS NEVER WITH US
ANYWAY SO HE WAS BASICALLY LIKE
A GIRL VOTE.
(LAUGHS)
MIKE, I'M GLAD HE'S GONE.
HE WAS GUNNING FOR ME FROM DAY
ONE AND I SOT GOT SICK OF HIM.
FOR ME TO HAVE MIKE GONE, THAT'S
FINE.
BUT IT IS SIX GIRLS AND THEY
COULD VERY WELL SAY LISTEN,
LET'S GET RID OF TROY AND JAY
BECAUSE THEY'VE WON THE LAST TWO
IMMUNTIES AND THEY'RE STRONG
AND THEY'RE GOING TO GET VOTES
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
SO PART OF ME IS LIKE, GEEZ, ARE
THEY TELLING ME THE TRUTH?
IF KIM AND CHELSEA AND
SABRINA AND CATHY THEY'RE JUST
GOING TO, YOU KNOW, WALTZ ON
INTO, LIKE, THE FINALS,
SOMETHING MAJOR COULD HAPPEN IF
ANY ONE OF US FIND AN IDOL.
THERE'S A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
OUT THERE.
(LAUGHS)
ALL IT TAKES IS ONE OF OUR VOTES
TO GET RID OF A KIM OR A CHELSEA
OR A SABRINA OR A STRONG PLAYER
AND THEN IT'S BASICALLY... IT
COULD BE YOU, ME, JAY, CHRISTIE
THAT AND LEIF AND THAT'S FIVE.
IT WOULD BE FIVE AGAINST
FREAKING FOUR.
IT AIN'T GONNA WORK THAT WAY,
I DON'T THINK.
(LAUGHS)
I'M JUST SAYING, I'M JUST
SAYING.
I THINK YOU HAVE TO START
WINNING ALL THE IMMUNITY.
OKAY, FINE.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS BUT I HAVE
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL WHICH I'M
BANKING ON IF I SEE SOMETHING
FISHY GOING ON WITH KIM AND
CHELSEA.
I DON'T WANT TO BE BLINDSIDED
GOING OUT OF HERE.
SO IF THEY PULL THAT, THEY'RE
GOING TO GET THE FULL ON
SWITCHER-ROO.
TREEMAIL!
OH, MY GOSH!
ALL RIGHT.
IT SAYS "CARRY ALL OF THIS BACK
TO YOUR CAMP.
DO NOT OPEN THIS ENVELOPE UNTIL
ALL MEMBERS OF YOUR TRIBE ARE
TOGETHER."
WOW.
THE WHOLE TRIBE WENT TO
TREEMAIL AND WE SAW, LIKE, THIS
BIG POLE, WE SAW SOME, LIKE,
BALLS WITH STRING AND WE WERE,
LIKE, "OH, COOL, SO WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE A CHALLENGE HERE ON THE
ISLAND" WHICH IS GREAT WHICH
MEAN WE DON'T HAVE TO GO
ANYWHERE, TRY TO WALK 50 MILES
SOMEWHERE.
ALL RIGHTY.
"TODAY YOU WILL COMPETE AN ALL
DO IT YOURSELF REWARD CHALLENGE.
YOU WILL DIVIDE YOURSELF INTO
TWO TEAMS."
IT WAS BASICALLY A GAME THAT
INVOLVED A NUMBERING SYSTEM OF
PEGS THAT WENT FROM ONE TO FIVE
POINTS AND THE WAY YOU ACHIEVE
POINTS WAS TO THROW A BOW US
WILL HOPING TO GET THE HIGHEST
NUMB SPWERS YOU WANT TO GET IT
AROUND ONE OF THE PEGS.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
THE WINNING TRIBE WILL RECEIVE A
BOAT RIDE TO A SECLUDED ISLAND
WHERE THEY WILL BE TREATED TO A
LOCAL BARBECUE FEST.
OH, MY GOD!
I WANT TO EAT.
IT'S FOR THE WINNERS ONLY.
SHOULD WE DRAW FIRST?
WE CAN PRACTICE.
WE'RE DRAWING.
READY?
DON'T SHOW IT.
OH, YOU'RE FEELING AROUND.
OH, YEAH.
UH-HUH.
OH, I GUESS I'LL GO LAST.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
ALL RIGHT, I NEED THE REDS TO
COME OVER HERE.
BLACKS.
SO WE RANDOMLY DREW ROCKS AND
ON MY TEAM WAS TROY, JAY,
TARZAN, KAT, AND MYSELF.
WE JUST NEED TO GET THOSE
POINTS.
AND THE OTHER TEAM WERE ALL
THE GIRLS AND LEIF LEFT OVER.
TROYZAN PROBST IS HOSTING THE
CHALLENGE.
SO HERE WE ARE, FOLKS.
WE HAVE A GREAT TEAM AND WE HAVE
AN OKAY TEAM.
(LAUGHTER)
I LOVE TROY LIKE COOKED FOOD
BUT HE IS NOBODY'S HOST AT ALL.
I THINK HE JUST NOMINATED
HIMSELF OR SOMEONE SAID IT AND
NO ONE ELSE OBJECTED.
JAY WANT THIS IS BARBECUE
MORE THAN HE CAN TASTE IT.
BIG JAY.
HE GETS THE FOUR AND GOES A
LITTLE LONG.
SORRY, JAY.
KIM IS UP NOW.
OH!
SHE HITS THE MIDDLE AND NOTHING.
SO IT'S 0-0 AFTER ROUND ONE.
KAT IS UP.
GOOD KAT!
GOOD JOB.
THEY TAKE THE LEAD 2-0.
READ TEAM LEADS.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
OH!
OH, WIDE!
0.
TROYZAN IS UP.
I'LL HOLD YOUR STICK,
TROYZAN.
HOLD MY STICK.
TAKE YOUR TIME LIKE I DID.
ALL RIGHT.
OH!
ALL RIGHT CHELSEA.
COME ON, CHELSEA.
OH, HITS THE FOUR AND BOUNCES
OFF!
THE CROWD GOES WILD!
AND A RELIEF COMES OVER FOR THE
RED TEAM!
TARZAN!
TARZAN MAY BE THE BEST PLAYER
HERE.
TARZAN, THIS IS FOR YOUR
FIRST REWARD.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
SO THAT'S 6-0.
CHRISTINA, LET'S SEE WHAT SHE'S
MADE OF.
1.
PUTS HER TEAM ON THE BOARD.
ALICIA'S SCORE COULD PULL IT
OUT.
OH!
0 FOR ALICIA.
SABRINA WITH THE LAST THROW.
I'M THE LAST PERSON TO GO IN
THE GAME.
THE HIGHEST YOU CAN SCORE ON THE
BOARD IS A 5 SO I HAVE TO GET A
FIVE IN ORDER TO TIE IT.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO LET MY
TEAM DOWN.
I'M NOT DOUBTING MYSELF BUT JUST
LIKE LORD, REALLY?
NO!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
BARBECUE!
TARZAN THE ALL STAR!
FINALLY!
YAY!
OKAY, SO THAT'S IT, FOLKS,
THANKS FOR COMING AND GET READY
FOR A BOAT RIDE.
PROTEIN!
BARBECUE!
OH, THIS IS AMAZING!
(APPLAUSE)
GOOD JOB, GUYS, GREAT JOB.
WHAT IS THAT?
RUM!
OH, IT'S RUM!
YEAH, I WANT RUM!
RUM AND COCOA, BABY.
I WANT A COCONUT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
I WAS, LIKE, YEAH, JUST GET
AWAY FROM THE GAME, GO TO SOME
ISLAND WITH THE GREATEST COCONUT
RUM DRINK I'VE EVER HAD IN
MY
LIFE.
THAT DOES TASTE GOOD, I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT.
SO WE WERE EXCITED.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
YEAH, WE'RE DRUNK ON RUM!
TARZAN, HOW DOES IT FEEL TO
GO ON YOUR FIRST REWARD?
WONDERFUL.
ON OUR OWN ISLAND.
IT IS OUR OWN ISLAND.
LOOK AT THIS THING.
YEAH, BABY, WE'VE REACHED
PARADISE.
WE LAND IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
SOUTH PACIFIC.
COCONUT RUM ALL AROUND.
CHEERS!
HEY, CAPTAIN.
IF WE COULD STAY HERE A NIGHT
I'D BE GOLDEN.
LET'S GET THE GIRLS ALL DRUNK.
YOU WANT ANOTHER COCONUT?
BRING ON THE RUM THERE, LAD.
CATCH YOUR COCONUT.
SKINNY DIPPING IN TEN
MINUTES, EVERYBODY!
I CAN'T WAIT TO EAT
SOMETHING.
IT LOOKS LIKE DECENT FISH.
I'M SALIVATING RIGHT NOW AS I'M
STANDING HERE BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
HAD ANY PROTEIN FOR 23 DAYS.
SOME BEAUTIFUL CRABS COLOR WISE
AND ARCHITECTURALLY.
NOW HE'S COOKING THE FISH.
A LOT OF FISH, HUH?
LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THAT SUCKER!
(WHISTLES)
JAY, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING
RIGHT NOW?
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
WELL, I WAS MAD YESTERDAY...
I WASN'T REALLY MAD BUT I DIDN'T
REALLY WANT TO SEND MIKE HOME.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE CHRISTIE
THAT OR ALICIA BEFORE HIM.
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T WANT TO SEND
ANOTHER DUDE HOME AND THEN,
LIKE, OH, WELL, OUR ALLIANCE,
OUR GIRLS FLIP ON US OR
SOMETHING.
WE'RE HESITANT.
ME AND KAT WERE TALKING AND I
WANTED TO MAKE SURE SHE'S ON THE
SAME PAGE WITH ME BECAUSE AT
THIS POINT IT'S HARD TO TRUST
ANYBODY.
AND IF SOMEBODY HAS NUMBERS ON
YOU, IT'S DEFINITELY HARD TO
TRUST THEM.
YOU KNOW, ALICIA, CHRISTINA,
TARZAN AND LEIF ALL HAVE TO GO
BEFORE WE DO.
I KNOW.
WE NEED TO STICK TOGETHER.
I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT OUR ALLIANCE
SAID THEY WAS GOING TO DO.
LET'S DO IT.
LET'S SEND MANONO HOME AND STICK
WITH THE PLAN.
WHICH IS THE PLAN.
GUYS, FOOD'S READY.
I'M COMING!
I'M A LITTLE SUSPICIOUS THAT THE
GIRLS ARE PLAYING TRICKS WITH
US.
WOW, THAT IS SO GOOD!
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT THE
CHICKEN.
THERE'S DEFINITELY GOING TO
BE BLIND SIDES COMING UP.
I JUST HOPE IT'S NOT ME.
DO YOU NOT?
MIKE WENT OUT AND THE GIRLS ARE
AHEAD.
I FEEL BAD BECAUSE, LIKE, I
THINK DEEP DOWN THEY KNOW THEY
MADE THE WRONG CHOICE ALREADY.
THEY HAVE TO BE REALLY WORRIED.
IT'S DEFINITELY A WIN-WIN TO
HAVE ANOTHER GUY GONE AND KNOW
THE WOMEN ARE IN THE MAJORITY
AND, YOU KNOW, MIKE'S GONE.
SO MY HOPE ALL ALONG HAS BEEN
EVERYBODY WILL THINK I'M JUST
KIND OF CALM AND SOFT SPOKEN AND
MAYBE A LITTLE FORGETTABLE AND
NOT CALLING THE SHOTS BUT I DO
THINK AT THE END OF THE GAME IF
I CAN SIT THERE WITH THE THREE I
THINK THE PEOPLE ON THE JURY
WILL KNOW THAT I WAS MAKING MOST
OF THESE DECISIONS.
I JUST THINK IT'S SMARTEST
FOR US TO GET RID OF JAY AND
TROY AND THEN GET RID OF TARZAN
AND LEIF.
OKAY, LET'S JUST SAY...
BUT WE NEED THEM TO BELIEVE
WITH ALL OF THEIR HEART THAT
THEY ARE NOT GOING HOME BECAUSE
IF THEY DON'T THEY WILL START...
THEY WILL FIND THAT IDOL OR
THEY'LL PULL SOME CRAP AND SO WE
JUST...
I AGREE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF I WANT
TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
DO YOU FEEL FUNKY ABOUT THAT?
I GOT A LOT GOING THROUGH MY
HEAD.
THE GIRLS HAD A DISCUSSION ON
THE BOAT THIS MORNING AND SAID
WHOEVER DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY
EITHER TROY OR JAY EITHER ONE OF
THEM HAS TO GO HOME NEXT.
WHICH IS KILLING ME RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE I'VE LOOKED TROY AND JAY
IN THE EYES AND SAID "YOU CAN
TRUST ME 100%."
AND LOOKING THEM IN THE EYES AND
TELLING THEM THEY CAN TRUST ME
AND THEN BETRAYING THEM, THAT'S
JUST NOT... THAT'S NOT ME AT
ALL.
DO YOU NOT THINK IT'S A GOOD
IDEA TO GET RID OF THEM?
I DON'T KNOW, I'VE GOT TO
THINK.
JAY COULD WIN EVERY IMMUNITY
FROM HERE ON IN.
AND TROY HAS A GOOD SHOT AT
DOING THAT, TOO.
SO THE MINUTE THEY DON'T WIN I
THINK THEY HAVE TO GO.
THIS IS LIKE THE PART OF THIS
GAME THAT SUCKS SO BAD.
IT SUCKS ASS.
THIS IS THE PART WHERE YOU
NEED TO TAKE YOUR HEART OUT OF
THE GAME AND PUT YOUR BRAIN BACK
IN THE GAME.
SERIOUSLY.
LIKE, CHELSEA GOT ALL
SENSITIVE.
YOU KNOW, THAT REALLY PISSED ME
OFF.
NO ONE TOLD YOU TO MIX WITH THE
BOYS ANYWAYS.
LIKE, WE WERE FINE WITHOUT THEM
AND THEN YOU GO OFF AND PROMISE
THEM THAT YOU'RE GOING TO CARRY
THEM TO THE TOP.
PLEASE.
SHE CAN'T GET OVER THE FACT
THAT WE HAVE TO ELIMINATE JAY
AND TROY.
WHAT SHE SAID WAS "I JUST DON'T
WANT TO BE A PART OF IT.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO THINK ABOUT
IT."
I WAS LIKE, DUDE, WHAT IS WRONG
WITH YOU?
WE COULD BE FINAL THREE OR FOUR.
SO NEXT TO GO HAS TO BE A BIG
MOVE.
EXACTLY.
WE CAN'T HAVE A LEAK OR CRACK
IN THE ALLIANCE.
EXACTLY.
AT ALL.
I MEAN, WE CAN SO GO OUT WITH
A BANG WITH ALL GIRLS.
WE CAN NOT HAVE ALL GUYS.
I KNOW, AND WE WILL HAVE
THREE AT... THE FINAL THREE?
DUDE.
LET'S TAKE IT WAY BACK TO DAY
ONE.
WE FORMED THIS ALLIANCE.
THIS IS WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
STICK WITH.
WE WANT TO GO TO THE END.
GOING TO THE END REQUIRES SOME
BIG-GIRL DECISIONS.
YOU'VE GOT TO PUT ON YOUR
BIG-GIRL PANTIES AND MAKE A
BIG-GIRL DECISION.
YOU KNEW IT WAS GOING TO HAVE TO
COME TO THIS.
YOU VOTING MIKE OUT, I
COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT THE ORIGINAL PLAN WAS FOR US
TO STICK TOGETHER.
IF WE STRAY FROM THAT, THEN IF
WE GET MIXED UP OR LET PEOPLE IN
AND SCREW US UP, WHO KNOWS WHAT
WILL HAPPEN.
THAT DON'T GUARANTEE US CRAP.
THEY NEED TO PICK OFF A FEW
GIRLS TO LET US KNOW THEY'RE ON
BOARD.
CHRISTINA AND LISA HAVE TO GO AT
SOME POINT SOON.
NEXT ON BOARD IS ALICIA.
OKAY.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED
ALICIA NEEDS TO GO BEFORE
CHRISTIE THAT.
ALICIA'S MORE KIND OF TWO-SIDED
WORKING WITH THE GUYS AND GIRL
SO TO ME SHE'S MORE OF A THREAT.
SHE'S REAL TIGHT WITH KAT.
I DON'T TRUST THAT.
THINK ABOUT IT.
IF WE STICK TOGETHER ME AND YOU
IN THE FINAL FOUR.
YEAH.
DUDE, THAT'S JUST... AND WE HAVE
A GREAT CHANCE, TOO.
WE CAN WIN EVERY FREAKING
IMMUNITY.
SERIOUSLY.
ME AND TROY ARE GOOD.
WE'RE STILL THINKING ME AND HIM
ARE GOING TO WORK TOGETHER FOR A
REAL LONG TIME.
HE THINKS I'M COMFORTABLE
SITTING IN THE END WITH HIM.
I'M GOING TO LET HIM KEEP
THINKING THAT.
BUT HE'S DANGEROUS AND YOU DON'T
WANT TO SIT IN THE END WITH HIM
BECAUSE EVERYBODY LIKES HIM, HE
SEEMS LIKE HE CAN TELL A STORY
BETTER THAN ANYBODY.
BUT KIM AND CHELSEA, THOSE ARE
MY FINAL TWO GIRLS I'M TRYING TO
WORK WITH.
SO YOU HAVE TO TRUST THEM A
LITTLE BIT BUT AT THE SAME TIME
YOU GET... YOU'VE STILL GOT TO
KEEP THEM AS CLOSE AS THE ENEMY
AROUND HERE.
YOU KNOW, THE LAST TWO HAVE BEEN
JONAS AND MIKE AND THE PLAN IS
TO GET RID OF THE REST OF
MANONO, SO THAT PUTS CHRISTIE
THAT AND ALICIA ON THE BLOCK.
OKAY.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE THAT
WE'RE GOING TO GO WITH ALICIA.
I HAVEN'T TALKED TO THE REST OF
OUR ALLIANCE, BUT I CHITCHATTED
WITH TROY.
AND SHE'S WEAKER THAN WHO?
SHE'S A THREAT.
SHE'S A MANONO.
SHE WORKS BOTH SIDES.
IT NEEDS TO BE HER TOMORROW.
I HAD TO SACRIFICE.
TROY HAD TO SACRIFICE.
WE NEED YOU TO MOVE FORWARD.
ARE YOU DOWN WITH THAT?
WHAT AM I GOING TO SAY, NO?
DROP IT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL LET ME GET
CONFIRMATION FROM EVERYBODY.
I REALLY DO APPRECIATE JAY AND I
REALLY DO LIKE HIM A LOT BUT I
CAN'T THINK WITH MY HEART AND
NEITHER CAN CHELSEA, NEITHER CAN
SABRINA AND KIM.
WE HAVE TO THINK WITH OUR MIND.
STRATEGICALLY THAT'S HOW PEOPLE
WIN WITH THIS GAME.
SO LET'S GET IT STRAIGHT.
I JUST TOLD KAT THAT I WAS ON
BOARD FOR ALICIA.
ARE YOU?
YEAH.
OKAY.
SHE JUST WANTED CONFIRMATION.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
IS THAT COOL?
YES.
SO WE CAN MAKE THAT SET AND
NOT DERIVE FROM IT.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
ONE'S ALICIA, TWO IS
CHRISTINA.
ALL RIGHT.
IT JUST SUCKS.
I REALLY MADE SOME CLOSE
RELATIONSHIPS WITH THE GUYS AND
JAY'S ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE THAT'S
VERY HARD TO LOOK HIM IN THE EYE
AND LIE TO HIM.
FORTUNATELY THERE'S, LIKE, FOUR
GIRLS STANDING THERE AND I
DIDN'T REALLY HAVE TO LOOK AT
HIM IN HIS EYE AND SAY "I
PROMISE THIS IS WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN."
BUT I JUST HATE TO BE THAT
DECEITFUL.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN DO THIS.
OH, I KNOW.
SO WE HAVE TO TAKE OUT TROY OR
JAY AND, LIKE, TELL THE GUYS
IT'S YOU.
I JUST FEEL LIKE THAT'S THE ONLY
WAY SO DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE SO SOLID.
WE'RE JUST PLAYING IT ALL THE
WAY HOME AND WHOEVER DOESN'T WIN
IMMUNITY, TROY OR JAY, IS GOING
HOME.
SO JUST DON'T FREAK OUT.
OKAY.
JUST BE YOURSELF.
JAY TOLD US ALL THAT HE
THOUGHT ALICIA SHOULD GO HOME
TONIGHT AND WE ALL JUST NODDED
AND AGREED AND SAID YES BUT
THAT'S DEFINITELY NOT HAPPENING.
JUST STAY CALM AND YOU'RE SO
SET.
OKAY.
I'M READY TO DRAW THE LINE.
LIKE, IT'S BEEN MUDDY FOR LONG
ENOUGH AND I FEEL LIKE IT'S TIME
FOR THE GUYS TO KNOW WHERE THE
WOMEN STAND.
I'M DEAD SERIOUS.
ALL RIGHT.
KIM AND ALICIA WERE ON THE
BEACH WATCHING BOWLS.
WHAT'S GOING ON.
WHAT'S... WHAT ARE THEY TALKING
ABOUT?
I MEAN, IF THE GIRLS WERE SMART
AND THEY GOT SIX OF THEM, IT
WOULDN'T BE HARD JUST TO KNOCK
OFF ME OR JAY.
IT WOULDN'T BE THAT HARD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK TODAY
HOLDS?
FOR THE CHALLENGE?
YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU WOULDN'T SKIP A CHALLENGE
OR COME OFF OF IT IF FOOD WERE
BROUGHT OUT?
NO.
I JUST FEEL LIKE... I STILL FEEL
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE KIM OR
CHELSEA WOULD BE, LIKE, YOU
KNOW, IT WOULDN'T BE HARD FOR
THEM JUST TO FREAKING BRING
ALICIA.
EVERYBODY'S ON THE SAME PAGE.
WE'RE WRITING DOWN ALICIA.
GOD, I JUST WANT THEM TO TRY
TO PULL SOME FAST MOVE ON THIS
ONE.
NO, I DON'T... I REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY DON'T SEE THAT
HAPPENING.
TROY'S JUST CONCERNED THAT THE
WOMEN HAVE THE NUMBERS.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO BLIND
SIDE HIM.
BUT WE HAD A LITTLE POWWOW,
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE ALICIA OUT
AS OUR FIRST CHOICE.
I TRUST MY TWO GIRLS.
TREEMAIL!
IS.
AND RIGHT NOW HE JUST NEEDS
TO CALM DOWN.
WITH TEN SURVIVORS LEFT IT'S
ANYBODY'S BET.
ONE WILL GET IMMUNITY, THE REST
WILL JUST GET WET.
JAY SEEMS TO THINK LIKE, NO, I
THINK EVERYTHING'S FINE, I THINK
THEY WANT ALICIA, I TRUST THEM,
I THINK IT'S OKAY.
BUT I DON'T FEEL THE SAME WAY.
SO I FEEL LIKE I REALLY HAVE TO
WIN.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JAY, GIVE IT UP.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IS A
"SURVIVOR" CLASSIC.
YOU WILL STAND BAREFOOT ON A
SMALL WOODEN PERCH.
YOUR HAND WILL BE TETHERED TO A
BUCKET.
WHEN YOUR ARM DROPS YOU'RE OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A 1-9 SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
TO MAKE IT MORE INTERESTING, I'M
GOING TO TRY TO TEMPT YOU WITH
FOOD ITEMS.
YEAH!
IF YOU TAKE THE TEMPTATION
YOU LOSE YOUR SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
THIS CHALLENGE IS OFFICIALLY ON.
TARZAN FIRST ONE OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE A LOT OF FAITH
YOU WERE GOING LAST, DID YOU.
NOPE.
Jeff: IS THE FEET?
FAILURE.
Jeff: JUST GENERAL FAILURE.
WE ARE DOWN TO NINE PEOPLE IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
I HAVE YOUR FIRST ITEM.
AND BEFORE I CAN EVEN GET TO IT,
CHRISTINA IS OUT.
DAMN IT!
Jeff: TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH AND YOU CAN SEE WHAT YOU
MISSED OUT ON.
IF YOU'RE SURE YOU'RE SAFE
TONIGHT YOU CAN ENJOY TWO
COOKIES AND A NICE GLASS OF
MILK.
I'M OUT, JEFF.
I'M OUT.
Jeff: SABRINA WANTS OUT.
SABRINA IS OUT.
NOBODY ELSE EVEN GETS TO SHARE
IN THIS.
SHE TOOK IT ALL.
SABRINA, I HATE YOU!
I HATE YOU, TOO.
Jeff: SO SABRINA, YOU ARE
CLEARLY FEELING VERY SAFE.
OH, MY GOD.
IF YOU HAVE THAT PLATE RIGHT
NOW I WANT IT.
Jeff: ALICIA WANTS WHAT'S
NEXT AND YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT IT IS.
YOU TAKE THAT FOOD, I'M GOING
TO VOTE YOU OUT.
Jeff: COOKIES WERE GOOD.
CUPCAKES ARE ALWAYS BETTER.
WOW!
NO.
I'LL STEP DOWN.
I'M STEPPING DOWN.
Jeff: IT'S KIM AND KAT.
KIM AND KAT MUST FEEL VERY SAFE.
CHELSEA, I'LL JUMP OFF ON THE
NEXT FOOD ONE AND JAY WILL COME
OFF.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS OUTLAST
THE OTHER GUYS.
I THINK THAT'S B. S +áFPL.
I CAN LAST LONG, BUT I'M
LETTING YOU KNOW, CHELSEA, I
WILL JUMP OFF FOR YOU.
THANKS.
Jeff: WAIT, LET ME MAKE
SURE I GOT THIS RIGHT.
YOU COULD LAST LONG BUT YOU'RE
GOING TO CHOOSE NOT TO SO THAT
CHELSEA CAN.
IF SHE WANTS TO WIN THIS ONE
REALLY BAD I'LL LET HER WIN IT.
YOU'LL LET ME OR YOU JUST
WANT SOME DAMN FOOD!
(LAUGHS)
Jeff: GONNA AMP UP THE
SWEET FACTOR A LITTLE MORE.
I WANT IT!
Jeff: ALICIA, YOU WANT IT
SIGHT UNSEEN?
I WANT IT.
Jeff: STEP OFF THAT
CHALLENGE.
ALICIA'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT IT
IS, GIRL!
Jeff: REMEMBER, CHELSEA,
SHE DID THIS AS A FAVOR TO YOU.
Jeff: ALICIA, YOU GAVE UP
IMMUNITY.
HERE'S WHAT YOU GAVE IT UP FOR.
OH, MAN!
Jeff: A BOWL FULL OF CANDY
AND CHOCOLATE.
I'M GOOD!
Jeff: TIME TO FIND OUT WHO
REALLY WANTS TO FIGHT FOR
IMMUNITY AND WHO'S WAITING FOR
SOMETHING REALLY HUGE TO STEP
DOWN.
Jeff: FOUR PEOPLE LEFT IN
THIS CHALLENGE FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY WHILE SIX PEOPLE OVER
HERE ARE SURE THEY DON'T NEED
IT.
"I DON'T NEED IMMUNITY.
I'M GOOD TO GO!"
LEIF TRYING TO KEEP THE BLOOD
MOVING.
PUMPING THAT FIST.
TROY, YOU'RE SHAKING.
TROYZAN WITH A NEAR FATAL
MISTAKE.
OH, TROYZAN LOSES HIS BALANCE.
YES!
Jeff: TROYZAN IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY TONIGHT.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO THREE.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE AND A
GUARANTEED 1-9 SHOT AT WINNING
THIS GAME.
YOU WANT TO GIVE IT UP FOR
CHICKEN WINGS AND STPWHAOER.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: JAY IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE AND WE ARE DOWN TO
TWO.
HE DON'T EVEN DRINK BEER!
(LAUGHS)
WOW.
GOOD JOB, JAY.
OOH, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
IS IT BETTER THAN THE CHICKEN
I CAUGHT?
LEIF ONCE AGAIN IN IT AT THE
END.
HE'S BEEN BATTLING FOR THESE
INDIVIDUAL CHALLENGES, HAS YET
TO WIN ONE.
CHELSEA SAID ALL ALONG "I'M NOT
STEPPING DOWN, I WANT TO WIN."
I'M STILL EMBARRASSED ABOUT
THAT PUZZLE SO I'M GOING TO BE
UP HERE ALL DAY, LEIF.
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO PROVE MYSELF.
I'VE GOT TO PROVE MYSELF,
TOO.
WELL, I CAN TELL YOU THIS, IF
YOU STEP DOWN IT MAKES YOU LESS
OF A THREAT.
Jeff: WOW, IT NEVER STOPS,
LEIF.
YOU CURIOUS ABOUT WHY SHE'S
SAYING THAT?
YEAH.
Jeff: CHELSEA'S SAYING
WINNING THIS ACTUALLY WORKS
AGAINST YOU.
WHO DO YOU TRUST?
I COULD STAY UP HERE ALL DAY
LONG.
Jeff: NEXT ITEM TO TRY TO
TEMPT YOU DOWN, THREE BURGERS, A
BOWL OF CHIPS AND A COLD BEER.
DO IT, CHELSEA, YOU HAVEN'T
EATEN.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE IT.
.Jeff: YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE
IT?
NOPE.
Jeff: CHELSEA NOT EVEN
TEMPTING HERSELF BY LOOKING.
LEIF, SHE'S TELLING YOU STEP
DOWN FROM THE CHALLENGE, TAKE A
BURGER AND MAKE YOURSELF LESS OF
A THREAT.
SOUNDS LIKE A GREAT DEAL IF YOU
BUY IT.
CHELSEA?
IS THAT TRUE?
YEAH, IT'S TRUE.
.IS THAT TRUE?
LOOK AT ME IN THE EYES, IT'S
TRUE.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
DO IT, BUDDY.
Jeff: LEIF STEPS OUT.
CHELSEA WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
GOOD JOB, CHELSEA!
Jeff: LEIF, HAVE A SEAT.
I JUST WANT A CHIP.
CHELSEA, EAT THE BURGER.
THAT WAS FUN.
Jeff: CHELSEA, COME ON OVER
HERE.
WELL EARNED AND YOU STILL HAVE A
MOUTHFUL OF FOOD.
THEY'RE SO NICE FOR SHARING.
Jeff: CHELSEA, SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GOOD JOB, CHELSEA.
YOU CAN NOT BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME WITH THIS AROUND YOUR
NECK.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GOOD JOB, CHELSEA.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
YEAH.
ONE OF THE BEST CHALLENGES EVER.
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
COULD NOT HAVE GONE BETTER FOR
ME.
IT WAS AWESOME.
I GOT TO EAT CUPCAKES AND HAVE
MILK AND NOT PUT MYSELF OUT
THERE AS A HUGE THREAT WHICH I
WAS KIND OF STARTING TO FEEL A
LITTLE NERVOUS ABOUT.
I'M GLAD FOR CHELSEA TO TAKE
THAT ROLE TODAY.
YOU WERE, LIKE, I SAID, OH,
TROY.
I WAS STILL WANTING TO GO A
LITTLE FURTHER WITH JAY AND TROY
BUT I'M REALIZING NOW THAT THAT
WOULD BE AN IDIOT MOVE SO TO
TURN THIS QUICK ON THEM I HATE
TO BE THAT PERSON BUT I LOVE
MONEY SO... (LAUGHS)
I WAS PISSED OFF WHEN I FELL
OFF.
YEAH, YOU WERE.
TOOK MY THING AND THREW IT.
I JUST WANT TO COMPETE.
TROY RIGHT NOW IS OUR BIGGEST
THREAT BECAUSE HE WANTS TO WIN
THIS GAME SO BAD.
I THINK MORE THAN ANYONE HERE.
I HAD IN THE MY MIND LIKE I'M
GOING ON THE THIRD ONE.
JAY, ON THE OTHER HAND, GAVE
UP FOR FOOD.
HE THINKS HE'S SAFE.
TROY DIDN'T GIVE UP FOR FOOD SO
I THINK RIGHT NOW HE'S THE
SMARTEST PERSON TO TAKE OUT.
I THINK WE POTENTIALLY HAVE
EIGHT VOTES FOR TROY SO WE'RE
GOING TO THROW THREE VOTES AT
JAY JUST...?
IN CASE?
I HATE IT BUT, LIKE... I
THINK JUST IN CASE.
BECAUSE IF TROY PLAYS AN
IDOL.
THE SPLIT VOTE PLAN, ALWAYS
RISKY, MAKES ME NERVOUS.
I'D RATHER KNOW EVERYONE'S
VOTING FOR TROY BUT THERE'S A
CHANCE TROY WILL THROW OUT AN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
HE'S A STRATEGIC PLAYER AND
THINKING A LOT AND HE'S GOING TO
DO EVERYTHING HE CAN TO STAY IN
THIS GAME AND HE STILL HAS SOME
OPTIONS TODAY.
I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE LIKE
CHRISTINA AND TARZAN AND LEIF
ARE JUST HANGING ON RIDING THIS
THING OUT SO CHRISTINA, ALICIA,
WILL VOTE FOR JAY AND LEIF,
MYSELF, CHELSEA, SABRINA AND CAT
WILL VOTE FOR TROY.
HERE HE COMES.
JAY DOES?
YEAH.
PLEASE TELL ME I DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT NO CRAZINESS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
NO CRAZINESS.
NO BLONDNESS GOING ON.
HUH?
I WANT TO KNOW ABOUT ANY
BLOND STRATEGY GOING ON.
NOTHING CRAZY, EVERYBODY'S
GOOD.
OKAY.
COOL BEANS.
IT'S TROY.
BUT WE WANT TO SPLIT THE VOTE
JUST TO DOUBLE CHECK AND MAKE
SURE IN CASE HE PLAYS AN IDOL SO
WHY DON'T YOU AND TARZAN VOTE
FOR TROY.
I'LL TELL CHRISTIE THAT IT'S
TROY.
SO THREE JAY...
I'LL TALK TO LEIF AND
CHELSEA, KAT, SABRINA, MYSELF
AND TROY.
AND IF THEY PLAY AN IDOL
NOBODY GOES HOME.
IT WILL BE JAY INSTEAD OF TROY.
OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT VOTING ME OFF.
NO.
YOU KNOW, IF I WAS PLAYING
THE DEVIL'S ADVOCATE AND I'D SAY
IT WOULDN'T BE MUCH FOR THE
GIRLS JUST TO SAY..
RIGHT.
...LET'S TAKE TROY AND YAY.
I GET WHY Y'ALL FEEL...
TO ME IT STILL FEELS...
I FEEL THAT WAY WITH TARZAN,
LEIF, KAT AND ALICIA.
I DON'T TRUST TWO OF THOSE GIRLS
SO.
ANYWAY...
SO IT'S DEFINITELY ALICIA?
YOU SWEAR TO ME?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BLIND SIDE
ME?
NO!
LIKE THAT MY "SURVIVOR"
EXPERIENCE SUCKS!
WE'RE GOOD.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
KIM KEPT GOING LIKE "DON'T
WORRY."
ALMOST LIKE TOO MUCH.
I DON'T KNOW IT SEEMS FISHY.
LIKE, IF SHE WANTED TO GET ME
OUT, SHE'D WANT TO BE EXTRA SURE
THAT I FELT LIKE I WAS SAFE.
IT SOUNDED LIKE THAT A LITTLE
BIT.
THIS MAY GO INTO PLAY SOON.
IT DOESN'T SOUND RIGHT.
LIKE "YOU'RE SAFE, YOU'RE SAFE."
YOU ONLY HAVE TO SAY IT ONCE.
I THINK KIM AND CHELSEA ARE
PULLING ONE OVER ON US.
I HAVE AN IDOL, BRO, I'M PLAYING
IT.
IF THEY'RE PLAYING ME, I WANT
THE PERSON TO GO HOME.
I DON'T THINK NOBODY'S
PLAYING YOU, TROY.
I'VE GOT A FEELING THEY'RE
PLAYING ME.
I AIN'T HEARD THE SLIGHTEST
INKREUPB NATION.
THEY WOULDN'T TELL YOU
ANYWAY.
YOU'RE BASICALLY HOOKED TO ME.
YOU DO WHAT YOU WANT, MAN.
BUT I DON'T... ITY YOU'RE GOOD.
WOULD YOU VOTE FOR KIM?
I THINK IT'S SAFE TO JUST SAY
ALICIA BECAUSE I REALLY THINK
IT'S HER.
IF I GET TARZAN TO VOTE FOR
KIM AND CHRISTINA TO VOTE FOR
KIM?
I THINK YOU'RE SAFE, BRO.
OKAY.
I THINK YOU'RE SAFE.
THAT'S NEWS TO ME TROY HAS AN
IDOL.
I LOVE THE GUY TO DEATH, HE'S
LIKE MY BIG BROTHER BUT HE'S
DANGEROUS TROY WANT MISS TOE
VOTE FOR KIM.
I'M NOT VOTING KIM OUT BECAUSE
THAT'S MY FINAL THREE.
TELL CHRISTINA TO COME TALK TO
ME.
I KNEW IT WAS GOING TO HIT
THE FAN.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD BE
TONIGHT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I KNOW YOU GUYS ARE
ATTEMPTING TO BLIND SIDE TROY.
IF WE WERE WOULD YOU TELL
HIM?
NOPE.
BUT HE'S DEBATING ON PLAYING AN
IDOL.
I I FIGURED.
SO I THINK YOU GUYS SHOULD
VOTE ALICIA, GET HIS IDOL OUT
AND GET HIM NEXT TIME.
CHRISTINA.
WHO ARE YOU... WHO ARE YOU
VOTING FOR?
HE'S OVER THERE SWITCHING
VOTES RIGHT NOW.
HE'S TRYING TO GET TARZAN AND
CHRISTINA TO VOTE YOU AND HE
ASKED ME TO VOTE FOR YOU AND I
SAID I'M STICKING WITH ALICIA.
IF YOU ALL SOCIETY FOR HIM AND
HE PLAYS THE IDOL THE NEXT FOUR
VOTES ARE COMING YOUR WAY.
JAY JUST PUT THE FEAR OF GOD
ME ME.
TROY DOES HAVE AN IDOL.
HE'S PLANNING TO PLAY IT AND
SEND ME HOME AND I DON'T HAVE
TIME BEFORE TRIBAL COUNCIL COMES
TO GET TO EVERYONE.
SO HOPEFULLY WE HAVE ENOUGH
PEOPLE ON BOARD THAT DO ENOUGH
OF THE RIGHT THING THAT THE
RIGHT PERSON WILL GO HOME
TONIGHT.
Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JONAS AND MICHAEL VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
TROYZAN, IN THE LAST TWO TRIBAL
COUNCILS, TWO GUYS HAVE GONE
HOME, JONAS AND MICHAEL.
IS THAT A SIGN THAT MAYBE THIS
IS STILL A MEN VERSUS WOMEN
GAME?
I THOUGHT IT WAS COINCIDENCE
BUT AS DAYS GO ON, THE MORE I'M
THINKING IT'S STILL A LITTLE BIT
MEN/WOMEN.
Jeff: TARZAN, HOW DID THE
MEN LOSE CONTROL IF THIS IS,
INDEED, MEN VERSUS WOMEN?
WELL, THEY LOST THEIR WILL
SEVERAL DAYS AND THE ALLEGIANCE
WAS BROKEN AND NOW IT'S WOMEN
TWO-UP.
SO THE GIRLS ARE A LOT SMARTER
THAN THE BOYS.
Jeff: JAY, IS IT POSSIBLE
THAT IT'S JUST THE WAY THE
NUMBERS FELL THAT IT'S TWO GUYS?
I'M KIND OF WITH TROY ON
THIS.
MY HOPE OF GUYS AND GIRLS
MESHING AND JOINING A LITTLE
BIT, YOU KNOW, THERE'S A LOT OF
SCRAMBLING GOING ON TODAY AND I
DON'T FEEL AS SAFE AS I DID LAST
TIME SITTING HERE TONIGHT.
Jeff: ACTUALLY, LET ME ASK
EVERYONE ELSE HERE.
WHO HERE TONIGHT THINKS THEY
MIGHT BE IN TROUBLE?
KIM, JAY, TROYZAN.
NOBODY ELSE?
KIM, DOES THAT SURPRISE YOU,
WITH ALL THE SCRAMBLING JAY
TALKED ABOUT THAT THERE'S STILL
ONLY THREE PEOPLE THAT ARE
WORRIED?
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
I FELT SAFE AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, I FELT SAFE WHILE I
ATE AND AFTERWARDS JUST TODAY
THIS AFTERNOON AT CAMP THERE WAS
A FUNKY VIBE.
I THINK YOU UNDERESTIMATE HOW
PARANOID PEOPLE GET, THEY RUN
AROUND AND OTHER PEOPLE GET
PARANOID.
SO I STARTED FEELING A LOT LESS
SAFE AFTER THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE TODAY.
Jeff: CHELSEA, PARANOIA.
PARANOIA CAN REALLY WREAK HAVOC
ON A PLAN.
WHAT DO YOU DO IN THIS GAME TO
KEEP YOUR PLAN INTACT?
YOU KNOW, THERE'S A... AS
MUCH AS THIS GAME... YOU KNOW,
WE'VE ALL WATCHED IT AND WE KNOW
THAT PEOPLE ARE DISHONEST BUT
THERE COMES A POINT WHERE YOU
REALLY HAVE TO GO WITH YOUR GUT
AND JUST REALLY HOPE THAT PEOPLE
ARE BEING HONEST WITH YOU AND
JUST LOOK THEM IN THE EYES AND
JUST TELL THEM HOW YOU FEEL AND
HOPE THAT THEY'RE BEING HONEST
WHEN THEY RESPOND.
AND THAT'S ALL YOU CAN DO.
Jeff: TROYZAN, HOW MIXED UP
IS THIS GAME RIGHT NOW?
IN MY MIND IT'S MIXED UP LIKE
HELL.
Jeff: DID IT MIX UP BEFORE
THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE OR AFTER?
AFTER.
YOU KNOW, JUST BECAUSE YOU CAN
KIND OF START TO TELL LIKE WHO
DECIDES TO STEP OUT FIRST AND
GET FOOD, WHO APPLAUDS WHO WHEN
SOMEONE GOES OUT.
YOU KNOW, I NOTICED THAT WHEN I
WENT OUT EVERYBODY APPLAUDED
EVEN SOME OF THE TRIBE THAT I
THOUGHT WOULD BE ROOTING FOR ME
I THINK MIGHT BE ROOTING AGAINST
ME.
SO THAT MEANT SOMETHING.
Jeff: CHELSEA, WHAT'S THE
TALK ABOUT HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOLS.
THE TALK IS THAT WE'RE AT DAY
25 AND NO ONE'S YET TO PULL ONE
OUT.
Jeff: IS THERE TALK ABOUT
WHO MIGHT HAVE ONE?
YEAH.
THERE'S SOME PEOPLE THAT ACT
SUSPICIOUS WITH THEIR BAGS OR
THEIR POCKETS LOOK A LITTLE MORE
FULL OR, YOU KNOW, STUFF LIKE
THAT.
BUT YOU NEVER KNOW WHO REALLY
HAS IT.
Jeff: ALICIA, WHAT ABOUT
YOU?
DO YOU WATCH PEOPLE, HOW THEY
PICK UP THEIR BAG OR MAYBE
WHAT'S IN THEIR POCKETS?
OH, DEFINITELY.
I NOTICE WHO TAKES THEIR BAGS TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND WHO DOESN'T.
I NOTICE WHAT SHORTS ARE WORN
TODAY AND WHAT SHORTS AREN'T
BEING WORN TODAY, YOU KNOW?
Jeff: WHO DO YOU NOTICE
WEARING DIFFERENT SHORTS?
THE MEN.
(LAUGHS)
THEY'RE NOT IN THEIR SWIMMING
TRUNKS AND HE'S GOT A LOT OF
POCKETS THERE.
Jeff: SO YOU'RE POINTING TO
TROYZAN SAYING "THESE AREN'T THE
SHORT HE IS NORMALLY WEARS"?
NO, HE HAD ON SWIMMING
TRUNKS.
Jeff: TARZAN, WHAT DO YOU
ANTICIPATE HAPPENING AFTER
TONIGHT'S VOTE?
I THINK THE ALLIANCE THAT I
KNOW OF IS GOING TO STRENGTHEN
AND THE FAITH WILL BE RESTORED
AND THERE WILL BE A POWERHOUSE
THAT WILL TAKE THEM TO THE END.
IF PEOPLE JUST DO WHAT THEY SAY
THEY WERE GOING TO DO BEFORE WE
GOT HERE.
AND OTHER THAN THAT, THE GAME IS
AFOOT.
(LAUGHTER)
Jeff: ON THAT NOTE, CHELSEA
HAS IMMUNITY.
YOU CAN NOT VOTE FOR CHELSEA.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
TARZAN, YOU'RE UP.
I TOLD YOU NOT TO STEP DOWN.
SORRY, KIM.
YOU'RE THE STRONGEST PLAYER,
HAVE TO SEE YOU GO.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO DO
THIS BUT I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
I LOVE YOU, MONKEY MAN.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
JEFF...
SOME OF THE DUMBEST MOVES IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY HAVE BEEN
MADE WHEN SOMEONE GETS VOTED OUT
AND HAS THIS IN THEIR POCKET AND
THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE ME.
I'M NOT GOING TO JOIN THAT
GROUP.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST TROYZAN
WILL NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, TROY.
DOES NOT COUNT.
TROY.
KIM.
ONE VOTE KIM.
JAY.
ONE VOTE JAY.
ALICIA.
ONE VOTE ALICIA.
JAY.
TWO VOTES JAY; ONE VOTE KIM; ONE
VOTE ALICIA.
ALICIA.
TWO VOTES JAY; TWO VOTES ALICIA;
ONE VOTE KIM.
JAY.
THAT'S THREE VOTES JAY; TWO
VOTES ALICIA; ONE VOTE KIM.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY, JAY.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JAY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, GIVEN THAT NEARLY HALF OF
YOU RECEIVED VOTES TONIGHT, IF
THERE WASN'T A REASON TO BE
PARANOID BEFORE, THERE CERTAINLY
IS NOW.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
OUTNUMBERED AND ALONE, TROYZAN
FIGHTS BACK.
(SCREAMING)
COME ON!
WE JUST WANT TO TAKE HIM DOWN
BUT EVERYONE KNOWS HE'S GOING TO
FIGHT AS HARD AS HE CAN.
I CAN JOIN YOU GUYS TO MAKE
FIVE.
YOU CAN PICK THEM ALL OFF.
YOU THINK YOU HAVE ME
OUTSMARTED.
THEY DON'T, YOU CAN NOT MESS
WITH TROYZAN.
THAT'S THE GAME FOR YOU, YOU
NEVER KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN OUT HERE.
YOU NEVER CAN TELL EXACTLY WHO'S
TELLING THE TRUTH.
YOU MAKE THE BEST DECISIONS
BASED ON WHAT YOU KNOW, GO WITH
YOUR GUT AS BEST AS POSSIBLE.
I HAD A GREAT TIME.
WOULDN'T TRADE IT FOR THE WORLD.
I TRIED TO PLAY THIS GAME AS
HONEST AS POSSIBLE, NOW I'M ON
THE SIDELINES.
I HAD AN EERIE FEELING COMING
IN HERE BUT I DIDN'T SEE MYSELF
GOING HOME.