Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
WE ARE SWITCHING TRIBES.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: AFTER AN UNEXPECTED
SWITCH, AN EVEN BATTLE BETWEEN
MEN AND WOMEN TURNED INTO A
LOPSIDED AFFAIR.
IT'S LIKE GREEK GODS VERSUS
PEASANTS.
Jeff: SALANI DREW ALL THE
STRENGTH LEAVING MANONO AS THE
CLEAR UNDERDOGS.
I GOT ON A TRIBE WITH PEOPLE
WHO SUCK!
Jeff: SALANI WINS REWARD!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
SALANI WINS IMMUNITY!
THE NEW SALANI WERE SEVEN STRONG
AND THEY DOMINATED EVERY
CHALLENGE.
SALANI WINS ICE CREAM REWARD!
WE'RE KICKING THEIR ASS.
I MEAN, BOTTOM LINE.
AT MANONO, LOSING WAS TAKING
A TOLL ON THE TRIBE BUT FOR
COLTON IT WAS BUSINESS AS USUAL.
YOU CAN QUIT OR YOU CAN JUMP
IN THAT FIRE, WHICH EVER IS MORE
CONVENIENT FOR YOU.
I'M RUNNING THIS ENTIRE SHOW
RIGHT NOW.
IF YOU CAN'T SEE THAT YOU ARE
HELEN KELLER.
Jeff: THEN A SUDDEN ILLNESS
PUT A STOP TO COLTON'S PLANS.
BUT EVEN A MEDICAL EVACUATION
COULDN'T STOP COLTON FROM
INFLUENCING THE GAME.
HE'S GOING TO KEEP THE
IMMUNITY IDOL FOR A SOUVENIR.
CALL ME A BAD PERSON BUT ALL I
KEPT THINKING WAS STRATEGY THE
WHOLE TIME.
Jeff: COLTON'S DEPARTURE
SENT BOTH TRIBES TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE THEY REUNITED AT
AN UNEXPECTED MERGE.
YOU CAN DROP YOUR BUFFS, WE
MERGED.
THE GAME HAS COME FULL CIRCLE
AND WE ARE EVEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SIX MEN AND SIX WOMEN.
12 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
FOOD!
OH, MY GOD, THERE'S CHEESE!
THIS SEEMS LIKE "SURVIVOR" TO
ME NOW.
IT'S A MERGE, IT'S ME AGAINST 11
PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED, THAT'S
WHAT I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR SO
BRING IT ON.
OH!
WOULD ANYBODY LIKE MY SIP?
I DON'T DRINK.
YOU CAN HAVE MINE.
I KNEW THE MERGE WAS COMING.
I'M SURE CHRISTINA... I DON'T
THINK SHE'LL BE IN THE GAME MUCH
LONGER.
IT'S CRAZY RIGHT NOW.
THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN CHRISTINA
GOING HOME AND NOT COLTON.
BY COLTON LEAVING, HE SCREWED ME
OVER, ESPECIALLY FACT THAT HE
DIDN'T GIVE ME HIS IMMUNITY IDOL
SO I HAVE TO START ALL OVER
AGAIN.
MAYBE I'LL GO BACK TO MY HOME
GIRLS AND CONTINUE THE GIRL
POWER RUN AND REALLY WIPE THE
GUYS OUT.
THE BACK STABBING IS GOING TO
BEGIN.
♪ ♪
WE NEED TO THINK OF A NEW
TRIBE NAME.
YEAH.
WELL TIKIANO.
TIKI IS GOD ANDANO IS YEAR.
IS THAT BREAKFAST?
COCONUT?
YEAH.
TODAY FOR BREAKFAST WE HAVE A
YOUNG COCONUT LIGHTLY
CARAMELIZED.
ALWAYS TASTE THE FIRST SERVING
FOR YOUR CLIENT.
AT THE END WE'RE GOING TO HIT IT
WITH SEA WATER SO BASICALLY
WE'RE TRYING TO MANIPULATE THE
FLAVOR OF THE COCONUT INTO THE
FLAVOR OF A POTATO CHIP.
THAT.
THAT'S AWESOME.
JONAS, I'M EXCITED TO HAVE YOU
HERE.
THANK YOU.
COFFEE TIME?
YUP.
HOW MANY'S GOING ON THE
FIRST, SHOWER IN.
IF I'M DRINKING IT I ONLY
NEED ONE SCOOP.
TARZAN, THIS IS FOR THE
PEOPLE THAT WANT IT.
I WANT IT.
YOU DIDN'T WIN THIS.
OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
SORRY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS A GENERAL
ONE OF THE 12 PEOPLE THAT MIGHT
WANT IT.
NOBODY EXPECTED A 12-MAN
MERGE.
IT WAS LIKE, OH, HERE WE ARE
AGAIN.
ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY ALL
TOGETHER.
AND FIRST THING I'M THINKING IS,
OH, MAN I HAVE TO LIVE WITH
TARZAN AGAIN.
ALL THESE PEOPLE YOU DON'T WANT
TO LIVE WITH ANYMORE AND NOW
THEY'RE BACK IN THE SAME TRIBE
AND IT'S JUST LIKE OH.
LAST DROP, ANYBODY?
EVEN THOUGH IT IS A ONE-MAN
GAME RIGHT NOW, I THINK SALANI'S
PEOPLE ARE VIEWING THIS AS A
CHANCE TO VOTE EVERYBODY ELSE
OUT OF THE OLD MANONO TRIBE
BECAUSE WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
OH, THIS IS GOING TO HURT MY
MOUTH.
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME YOU HAD
COFFEE, TARZAN?
LONG ENOUGH THAT I'M NO
LONGER ADDICTED.
YOU'RE GOING TO DRINK SOME
THOUGH, RIGHTING?
NO, YOU GUYS WON IT, IT'S
YOUR COFFEE.
I WAS HOPING THAT THE GUYS WOULD
BE SOLID AGAINST THE GIRLS BUT
NOW THIS MORNING I FRET IT AIN'T
SO.
CAN I BE PART OF THE TEAM?
WHO'S THE TEAM?
ME, JAY BIRD, TROY.
LEIF, JONAS?
RIGHT.
SIX GUYS; SIX GIRLS.
BUT WE HAVE A GIRL THAT WILL
DEFECT.
ALICIA, SHE'S BEEN COLTON'S
LITTLE GIRL.
RIGHT.
WE'RE ONE TRIBE NOW, THERE'S
BEEN A HUGE MERGE.
THE MANONO TRIBE ARE OUTNUMBERED
BY TWO.
TARZAN HE IS TRYING TO GET THE
GUYS TO STICK TOGETHER.
HE FEELS THAT IF THE GUYS STICK
TOGETHER AND USE ALICIA THAT THE
GUYS WILL BE THERE AT THE END.
YOU'VE BEEN WITH US ALL
ALONG, MIKE, SO I'M JUST HOPING
YOU STAY WITH US.
ARE YOU IN?
YEAH.
GUYS WERE BETTER TOGETHER.
RIGHT.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
YOU SURE IF.
I DON'T TRUST ANY OF THOSE GUYS
AND LIKE ANY OF THOSE GUYS BUT I
TOLD TARZAN I'M IN BUT I'M NOT
WITH TARZAN.
TARZAN DRIVES ME CRAZY.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
ONLY YOU ARE GOING TO BE DIVIDED
BACK INTO TWO TRIBES.
ON MY GO, ONE MEMBER OF EACH
TRIBE WILL RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES.
THEY'LL DIG UP A BAG OF PUZZLE
PIECES AND RACE BACK.
THEN THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL FOUR
BAGS THE TWO REMAINING TRIBE
MEMBERS WILL USE THOSE PIECES TO
SOLVE A PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
REWARD.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
YES.
Jeff: THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL ENJOY AN AFTERNOON OF PIZZA
AND COLD BEER.
OH, MANY I GOD!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
Jeff: PLUS A SECRET NOTE.
WE'RE GOING TO RANDOMLY DIVIDE
INTO TRIBES AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TRIBES FOR THIS
CHALLENGE ONLY.
ALICIA, JAY, SABRINA, CHELSEA,
CHRISTINA AND TROYZAN BATTLING
AGAINST LEIF, KAT, MICHAEL, KIM,
JONAS AND TARZAN.
FOR PIZZA AND BEER A SECRET
NOTE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GO, JAY, GO JAY!
Jeff: JAY AND LEIF THE
FIRST TWO GOT TO DO SOME
DIGGING.
ONE TRIBE SENT THEIR BIGGEST AND
STRONGEST GUY TO DIG THE HOLE.
THE OTHER TRIBE SENT THEIR
SMALLEST GUY.
DON'T LET THE LITTLE GUY BEAT
YOU!
GO!
Jeff: JAY IS ALREADY TRYING
TO SQUEEZE UNDER.
GOOD JOB!
Jeff: JAY IS THROUGH!
LEIF NOW GOING FACE FIRST.
THAT'S RIGHT!
GET THE BEER.
Jeff: LEIF IS STUCK.
LEIF IS LIKE A TURTLE BIRTHING
OUT OF THE SAND.
JAY DIGGING FOR THAT FIRST BAG
OF PUZZLE PIECES.
BLUE TRIBE SENT THE SMALLEST GUY
OUT AND IT MAY BE BACKFIRING
NOW.
KEEP GOING HARD!
EVERYTHING YOU GOT!
Jeff: JAY HAS THE FIRST BAG
OF PUZZLE PIECES.
HUGE LEAD RIGHT NOW FOR THE
ORANGE TRIBE.
WAY TO GO, JAY!
Jeff: LEIF WIGGLING THROUGH
THERE INCH BY INCH.
LEIF IS OUT NOW!
HE'S GOT SOME TIME TO MAKE UP.
GO, GO!
Jeff: CHELSEA NOW ON THE
COURSE FOR THE ORANGE TRIBE.
LEIF NOW STARTS DIGGING FOR HIS
FIRST BAG.
LEIF KEEP GOING, DIG, DIG.
Jeff: LEIF HAS THE FIRST
BAG FOR THE BLUE TRIBE.
HE'S HEADING BACK!
CHELSEA HAS THE SECOND BAG FOR
THE ORANGE TRIBE.
ON YOUR BACK!
COME ON, LEIF!
Jeff: LEIF GOES UNDER ON
HIS BACK THIS TIME.
MUCH EASIER.
LEIF IS EXHAUSTED.
COME ON, CHELSEA.
Jeff: KIM OUT ON THE COURSE
FOR THE BLUE TRIBE.
CHELSEA'S THROUGH WITH THE
SECOND BAG.
ALICIA HEADING OUT NOW FOR THE
ORANGE TRIBE.
KIM IS NOW STUCK JUST LIKE LEIF!
THAT SHOAL NOT BIG ENOUGH.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: KIM IS FREE NOW.
ALICIA STARTS WORK ON THE THIRD
BAG OF PUZZLE PIECES.
KIM NOW WORKING ON THE SECOND
BAG.
THERE ARE FOUR BAGS TOTAL.
ALICIA HAS THE THIRD BAG FOR THE
ORANGE TRIBE.
KIM STILL WORKING ON THE SECOND
BAG.
LET'S GO!
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: KIM HAS THE SECOND
BAG FOR THE BLUE TRIBE.
SABRINA NOW OUT ON THE COURSE.
COME ON, KIM!
KEEP PUSHING.
YOU'RE GETTING IT!
Jeff: KIM IS BACK WITH THE
SECOND BAG OF PUZZLE PIECES.
KAT IS NOW OUT ON THE COURSE.
SABRINA IS STUCK!
LET'S GO!
COME ON!
Jeff: KAT FLIES THROUGH THE
FIRST OBSTACLE.
KAT COULD MAKE UP SOME TIME FOR
THE BLUE TRIBE.
GO KAT, GO!
Jeff: SABRINA IS FREE NOW.
DIG, KAT!
DIG, DIG!
Jeff: SABRINA LOOKING AT
THAT FOURTH AND FINAL BAG.
KAT WORKING ON THE THIRD BAG FOR
THE BLUE TRIBE.
Jeff: NICE JOB, SABRINA,
THAT'S A LOT OF SAND!
Jeff: KAT HAS THE THIRD BAG
FOR THE BLUE TRIBE.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
MICHAEL THE BIGGEST GUY NOW HAS
TO MAKE HIS WAY UNDER THIS.
BLUE TRIBE SEEMS TO HAVE DONE IT
BACKWARDS.
MICHAEL IS THROUGH THE FIRST
OBSTACLE.
MICHAEL NEEDS TO MAKE UP SOME
TIME RIGHT NOW.
SABRINA HAS LOST A LOT OF THE
LEAD.
THE ORANGE TRIBE HAD.
DIG THAT SAND!
DIG IT!
YOU GOT IT!
SABRINA, YOU GOT IT, YES!
Jeff: SPWRAOE SPHA HAS THE
FOURTH BAG FOR THE ORANGE TRIBE.
MICHAEL THAT HAS FOURTH BAG FOR
THE BLUE TRIBE.
WE'VE GOT A RACE GOING.
GIVE IT EVERYTHING YOU GOT!
LET'S GO, MIKE!
Jeff: SABRINA TRYING TO
PULL HERSELF UNDER THAT LAST
OBSTACLE.
MICHAEL HAS GAINED ON HER.
MICHAEL HAS MADE UP ALL THE TIME
THE BLUE TRIBE HAS LOST FOR THIS
ENTIRE CHALLENGE.
SABRINA IS THROUGH.
MICHAEL IS THROUGH VERY QUICKLY.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
WHATEVER LEAD THE ORANGE TRIBE
HAD WAS LOST IN THAT FINAL ROUND
AND WE ARE NOW NECK IN NECK
TARZAN AND JONAS WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE FOR THE BLUE TRIBE.
TROYZAN AND CHRISTINA FOR THE
ORANGE TRIBE.
THIS IS IT.
FEEL FREE TO START WORKING,
TARZAN.
I AM.
Jeff: COMMUNICATION WILL BE
KEY IN WORKING TOGETHER ON THIS
PUZZLE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
Jeff: PIECES ARE ALL VERY
SIMILAR.
BEAUTIFUL!
Jeff: EVERYBODY CAN TASTE
THAT PIZZA.
THEY CAN IMAGINE THE COLD BEER.
TROYZAN AND CHRISTINA WORKING
TOGETHER VERY WELL.
TARZAN AND JONAS NOW STARTING TO
PULL AHEAD FOR THE BLUE TRIBE.
CHRISTINA AND TROYZAN, WHATEVER
MOMENTUM THEY HAD IS
EVAPORATING.
THERE IT IS.
Jeff: TARZAN WITH A PIECE
NOW.
I GOT A FEW PIECES, COME ON.
TARZAN, QUIT TALKING, DUDE.
Jeff: WE ARE VERY CLOSE
RIGHT NOW.
EITHER TRIBE COULD WIN THIS
CHALLENGE.
IT'S COMING DOWN THE LAST COUPLE
OF PIECES!
BOTH TRIBES DOWN THREE PIECES.
PIZZA, BEER ON THE LINE.
WHO WANTS IT?
THE ORANGE TRIBE WINS REWARD!
(SCREAMING)
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD!
(SCREAMING)
THIS IS MY ISLAND!
Jeff: NICE AFTERNOON
AWAITING YOU.
PIZZA, COLD BEER AS WELL AS THIS
NOTE WHICH YOU WILL READ AFTER
YOU FINISHED EATING.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT.
ENJOY THE AFTERNOON.
TARZAN, KAT, KIM, MICHAEL,
JONAS, LEIF, GOT FOR FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY LORD!
I'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT PIZZA
SINCE DAY ONE.
YOU GUYS, EVERYONE DID A
FANTASTIC EFFORT.
TO ENDURANCE.
THE CHALLENGE WE HAD TO DO TODAY
WAS A DOOZY.
IT WAS A NAIL-BITER BUT AT THE
VERY END WE WON.
THIS PIZZA COULD HAVE BEEN ICE
COLD AND I WOULD HAVE TORE IT
UP.
I DON'T CARE.
I KNOW GOOD PIZZA, I'VE BEEN
LIVING IN NEW YORK FOR TEN
YEARS.
ANYTHING OTHER THAN THIS DRY-ASS
RICE WE'RE EATING OUT HERE AND A
CHICKEN WE CATCH EVERY BLUE
MOON, IT'S GREAT SO PIZZA WAS
PRICELESS.
THEY COULD HAVE BROUGHT OUT
FRIED SKUNK.
(LAUGHTER)
(BELCHES)
OH, MY GOSH!
ROCK 'N ROLL!
ALL RIGHT, GUYS WE HAVE THIS.
WHAT DOES IT SAY?
IT SAYS "OPEN WHEN YOU'RE
FINISHED EATING BEFORE YOU GET
BACK TO CAMP."
ALL RIGHT.
"IMMUNITY IS THE ONLY WAY TO
GUARANTEE YOUR SAFETY IN THIS
GAME.
AS PART OF YOUR REWARD FOR
WINNING TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ONLY
YOU SIX WILL KNOW THAT THERE IS
YET ANOTHER IDOL HIDDEN BACK AT
CAMP."
THE LESS PEOPLE THAT KNOW
ABOUT THE IDOL THE MORE LIKELY
ONE OF US CAN FIND IT.
SO IF I WERE UP TO ME I WOULDN'T
GO BACK TO CAMP AND BE LIKE
"HEY, THE LETTER SAID THERE WAS
AN IDOL SOMEWHERE."
IT MAKES ME NERVOUS THAT THE
IDOL IS STILL OUT THERE.
MY BIGGEST CONCERN IS FOR
SOMEONE ON THE MANONO TRIBE TO
FIND THE IDOL GOING INTO THE
NEXT VOTE.
AND MESSING UP OUR NUMBERS.
BECAUSE WE CAN'T HAVE A SALANI
GO HOME.
I WANTED THAT PIZZA AND BEER
SO BAD.
I GOT SAND EVERY PART OF MY
BODY.
YOU TRYING TO TELL US YOU'RE
GOING TO BE POOPING SAND FOR THE
NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS?
WE NEED TO GET STUFF TOGETHER
HERE, YOU KNOW?
LIKE SUPPLIES?
OR, LIKE, THOUGHTS?
NO, JUST WHATEVER OUR PLAN
IS, YOU KNOW?
I THOUGHT TARZAN ALREADY
ESTABLISHED THAT.
WHAT WAS THAT?
THAT THE GUYS STICK TOGETHER
AND ALICIA IS THE SWING VOTE.
THAT'S KIND OF WEIRD THAT YOU
DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT THAT PLAN
IS.
YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT HE WAS SAYING BUT
HE SHOULD PROBABLY FILL YOU IN
WITH THE PLAN.
WE DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE TO
TALK.
I'LL ASK ABOUT THAT LATER ON.
APPARENTLY, THE BRIGHT TARZAN
GOES AND HAS A SECRET MEETING
WITH MIKE AND TELLS HIM THIS
PLAN WHICH I'M NOT EVEN AWARE
OF.
THE GUY MAKES ZERO SENSE.
HE'S A LOSE CANNON AND DOES
WHATEVER THE HELL HE WANTS WE
CAN'T HAVE THAT.
YOU TELL THE LEAST RELIABLE GUY
THE PLAN, DOES THAT MAKE SENSE
TOW-TO-YOU?
YEAH, BECAUSE WE NEED SIX
GUYS.
YOU TELL HIM RIGHT BEFORE THE
VOTE, NOT TWO DAYS BEFORE!
IF HE'S PLAYING BOTH SIDES, WHAT
IS HE GOING TO DO?
HE'S GOING TO TELL THE WOMEN AND
THEN WE'RE (BLEEP)ED.
THIS IS MY POINT.
WE NEED TO CONSULT AS AN
ALLIANCE BEFORE WE START
BLABBING.
I THOUGHT...
WHEN DID IT CHANGE AND WHY AM
I THE LAST GUY TO KNOW?
TWO DAYS AGO I TOLD YOU THAT
PLAN.
PLAN!
LISTEN TO ME, I'M NOT DONE
SPEAKING.
YOU ARE SUCH A CONFUSED
(BLEEP), I'M DONE TALKING WITH
YOU.
I'M DONE TALKING.
YOU'RE ACCUSING ME OF
SOMETHING RIGHT NOW.
DON'T (BLEEP)ING INTERRUPT
ME.
LISTEN TO ME FOR A SECOND!
STOP (BLEEP)ING INTERRUPTING ME.
I'M TIRED OF YOUR (BLEEP)ING
(BLEEP).
AND YOU TELLING ME... I'M NOT
EVEN IN THE (BLEEP)ING LOOP.
WELL YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S SO MUCH CONFUSION I'M
GOING TO DROP OUT OF THE TRIBE
AND YOU GUYS CONTINUE WITHOUT
ME.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
I'M DROPPING MY ALLEGIANCE WITH
YOU GUYS BECAUSE EVERY TIME I
TRY TO TELL YOU SOMETHING YOU
CONTRADICT MED, YOU DON'T
REMEMBER WHAT I SAY.
I'M DONE WITH IT.
WHAT ARE YOU FIGHTING ABOUT.
MISUNDERSTANDING.
JONAS, LET'S ADMIT IT.
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
DON'T TALK TO ME ANYMORE.
I'M OUT OF IT.
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD LUCK.
I'LL FALL ON THE SWORD.
I'M PERFECTLY WILLING TO DO IT.
I CAN ONLY PLAY THIS GAME SO
LONG BEFORE IT'S IRRITATING.
I DO NOT LIKE JONAS.
I DO NOT LIKE THAT GUY ANYMORE.
WHEN I SAY SOMETHING I MEAN IT
FROM MY HEART AND I DON'T GO
BACK ON IT.
CAN'T LOOK AT THAT FACE ANYMORE.
EVERYONE ALWAYS SLEEPS IN AND
I GET UP AT 4:00 IN THE MORNING
SO I'M GOING TO FIND THE IDOL.
THESE KNUCKLE HEADS AREN'T GOING
TO BE AWAKE FOR ANOTHER HOUR.
YES!
THAT'S IT!
(LAUGHS)
EARLY BIRD GETS THE IDOL AND
GETS THE POWER.
I HAD MY EYE ON THE TWO BIG
TREES CLOSE TO THE BEACH AND I
IT THIS JACKPOT.
TO FIND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, THAT'S LIKE WINNING THE
GOLD MEDAL.
GOD, I WANT TO, LIKES, WEAR IT.
TROYZAN IS SAFE!
THIS COULD BE A MILLION DOLLARS.
THIS IS CRAZY TO THINK ABOUT IT.
THIS COULD TAKE ME FREAKING FAR.
COME ON IN, GUYS!
SO IS THERE A NEW TRIBE NAME?
TIKIANO.
Jeff: WHAT'S IT MEAN?
WELL, TIKIANO MEANS GOD AND
ANO MEANS YEAR SO IT'S LIKE YEAR
OF THE GOD.
Jeff: READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, CHRISTINA,
I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NO MORE.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IS NOW WHAT
YOU SEE.
WITH THIS AROUND YOUR NECK AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU CAN'T BE
VOTED OUT.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
YOU WILL BE PERCHED ON A SMALL
LOG WHILE BALANCING A BALL ON A
WOODEN DISK.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS WE WILL ADD
MORE BALLS MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT.
IF AT ANY POINT A BALL DROPS OR
YOU FALL OFF THE PERCH YOU'RE
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMOONTY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL, SOMEBODY
WILL BE GOING HOME.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET STARTED,
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR DISK AND
YOUR FIRST BALL.
5-4-3-2-1.
EVERYBODY REMOVE YOUR HANDS.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
RIGHT AWAY A BIG BREEZE COMES
UP.
AND THAT CAUSES SOME PROBLEMS
FOR A FEW PEOPLE.
MAKE SURE THE DISK DOES NOT HIT
YOUR BODY.
THAT IS A NO-GO.
TARZAN IS FIRST OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
HE FALLS OFF THE PERCH.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE'RE DOWN TO 11.
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO HAVE TO WORK
HARD TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR BALL.
YOU ARE SAFE AND MOVING ON TO
THE NEXT ROUND.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY GRAB A
SECOND BALL NOW.
TAKE YOUR HANDS OFF NOW
EVERYBODY BALANCING TWO BALLS ON
THEIR DISK.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP CONCENTRATION
KEEP YOUR FOCUS.
CHRISTINA'S THE SECOND PERSON
OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO TEN PEOPLE
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
MICHAEL WITH BALLS HANGING ON
BOTH SIDES OF HIS DISK CAN'T
HANG IN THERE, MICHAEL IS OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE WE'RE DOWN TO
NINE.
EVEN IF YOU'RE ON THE EDGE, HANG
IN THERE.
CHELSEA BOTH BALLS DROP.
CHELSEA IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE
AND RIGHT BEHIND HER KIM LOSES
IS BALL.
KIM IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
SEVEN PEOPLE ARE DOWN.
SURVIVE THIS YOU MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
GRAB YOUR BALLS, EVERYBODY IS
SAFE.
THIRD AND FINAL ROUND.
EVERYBODY RELEASE YOUR HAND, THE
CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
WE WILL NOW GO UNTIL THERE'S
ONLY ONE PERSON LEFT.
ALICIA IS QUICKLY OUT AND WE ARE
DOWN TO SIX THIS WILL NOT BE AN
EASY WIN.
SUCH A SIMPLE LITTLE CHALLENGE
YOU COULD DO IT IN YOUR
BACKYARD.
ONLY DIFFERENCE, LOSE THIS
CHALLENGE YOU COULD BE GOING
HOME TONIGHT.
AND WITH THAT JAY FALLS OFF THE
PERCH.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO FIVE.
TROYZAN'S BALLS HAVEN'T MOVED IN
A LONG TIME.
(LAUGHS).
Jeff: GET YOUR
CONCENTRATION.
JONAS BALANCING TWO BALLS ON ONE
EDGE.
ONE BALL ON THE OTHER EDGE OF
HIS DISK.
JONAS CAN'T DO IT.
KNOW SKWRAS IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR.
BIG BREEZE STARTING TO COME IN.
SABRINA OUT OF THE CHALLENGE AND
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE.
TROYZAN, KAT, AND LEIF.
LEIF DROPS A BALL, LEIF IS OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
HIS SHOT AT IMMUNITY IS OVER.
YOU CAN SEE IT IN HIS FACE.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO PEOPLE LEFT:
TROYZAN AND KAT.
TROYZAN WITH A NICE RECOVERY KAT
STILL VERY SOLID.
TROYZAN STRUGGLING TO GET IT
BACK AND HE DOES.
NO MATTER HOW SOLID YOU FEEL IN
THIS GAME, YOU DO NOT WANT TO GO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL WITHOUT
IMMUNITY.
KAT STEPS OFF THE PERCH TROYZAN
WINS FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY!
MY MY LEG.
Jeff: TROYZAN, COME ON
OVER.
THIS IS CRAZY.
Jeff: WHAT'S CRAZY ABOUT
IT?
YOU KNOW HOW LONG I'VE WAITED
TO FEEL THIS THING, MAN?
IT'S LIKE WHAT THE HELL IS GOING
ON RIGHT NOW.
AND YOU'RE TOUCHING ME, JEFF
PROBST.
IT'S CRAZY.
Jeff: IT'S GETTING BETTER,
YOU'RE SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL AS WELL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 20
DAYS WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
GREAT JOB.
JONAS, I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
PULL IT OUT WITH YOUR CHEF
SKILLS.
GREAT JOB, BRO.
THANKS, BUDDY.
YOU DID GOOD.
WE'RE DEFINITELY GOING TO
HAVE TO TALK LATER.
I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO BE DOING SOME
SCRAMBLING ACTION.
YEAH.
THIS IS LIKE "SURVIVOR" TO
THE ULTIMATE.
I MEAN, I WON AN IMMUNITY TODAY,
I HAVE AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I'VE GOT A GROUP THAT I FEEL
SOLID, MY OLD SALANI WHO
BASICALLY HAVE BEEN PRETTY
STRAIGHTFORWARD WITH ME AND SO
WHATEVER THEY DECIDE TO DO
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
I THINK IT'S PRETTY PLAIN AND
SIMPLE THAT WE STICK TO SALANI
OR 7-5.
YEAH.
JUST PICK OFF THEIR FIVE
STRONGEST TO WEAKEST AND THEN
WE'RE BACK AT SALANI.
SO, LOOK, WE NEED TO FIGURE
OUT WHO WE WANT OFF I SAY JONAS
AALICIA.
WE CAN ASK AROUND, TO, BUT MAKE
JONAS THE FIRST CHOICE.
OKAY.
IT'S GUYS VERSUS GIRLS BUT THE
WAY I SEE IT IS WE KEEP IT
SALANI VERSUS MANONO WE SHOULD
TAKE OUT MANONO'S STRONGEST
PEOPLE FIRST.
I DON'T THINK THAT... WOULD
YOU GUYS BE COOL VOTING JONAS
FIRST?
LET'S GO JONAS FIRST.
JONAS IS FIRST.
I THINK JONAS IS THEIR
STRONGEST PLAYER RIGHT NOW.
WHICH I HATE BECAUSE HE'S A
GREAT COOK.
GREAT POSITIVE ATTITUDE.
FUN TO BE AROUND.
BUT JONAS I'M THINKING IS GOING
TO BE THE NEXT TO GO.
HEY, YOU.
NO ONE HAS COME UP TO ME.
COME UP TO ME, GIRLFRIEND.
I JUST THINK EVERYONE'S THINKING
JONAS BUT EVERYBODY'S LIKE "OH,
I HATE TO VOTE JONAS OUT HE'S SO
NICE AND HE COOKS GOOD SOUP."
I DON'T CARE WHETHER HE MAKES
A GREAT SOUP.
FOR TONIGHT'S VOTE WE WANT TO
VOTE JONAS OUT SINCE HE'S THE
BIGGEST THREAT AND KEEP
CHRISTINA AND ALICIA AROUND JUST
IN CASE WE NEED A GIRL'S
ALLIANCE.
TO GET A GUY OUT AND
PARTICULARLY ONE OF THE NEW
MANONO TRIBE MEMBERS IT LEAVES
THE GIRLS IN THE MAJORITY IT
LEAVES MY OLD SALANI TRIBE IN
THE MAJORITY AND GIVES ME TWO
GREAT OPTIONS MOVING FORWARD.
WHO DO YOU... ARE YOU LOOKING
AT RIGHT NOW?
HONESTLY I WAS THINKING JONAS
BECAUSE HE'S REAL SMART, REAL
CAPABLE.
I KNOW.
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT JONAS BECAUSE THEY
THINK THEY FEEL HE'S A BIG
THREAT AND HE'S THE SMARTEST OF
THE GUYS AND I WAS LIKE, GEEZ,
YOU GUYS, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WE'RE GOING TO LET THIS GUY GO?
HE FEEDS US PROERBGS SIDES ARE
FOR US, WHY NOW?
.
ARE YOU SERIOUS, DUDE?
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT HE?
UH-HUH.
THEY MENTIONED MY NAME.
YEAH, THEY DID.
WHY WOULD THEY WANT TO VOTE
ME?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
WHEN YOU HEAR YOUR NAME HAS
COME UP, YOU IMMEDIATELY THINK
OH, CRAP, I'M GOING HOME.
YEAH, I'M KIND OF GETTING THE
FEELING THAT I'M OUT OF THE
LOOP.
IT MAKES NO LOGICAL SENSE TO ME
STRATEGICALLY TO VOTE ME OUT
I'M, LIKE, THE LEAST THREATENING
GUY HERE.
THERE'S MIKE WHO'S THE MOST
DOMINANT PERSON AS FAR AS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES SO THEY WANT
TO KEEP HIM AROUND OVER ME AND
SO IMMEDIATELY I GO INTO
SURVIVAL MODE.
SO I JUST WANTED TO THROW YOU
THIS OUT.
I WAS OUT OF LINE LIKE
COMPLETELY WAS ACTING..
WE ALL GET...
I WAS RIDICULOUS AND I
APOLOGIZE.
YOU'RE APOLOGIZING?
REALLY.
THANK YOU.
WE HERE IN A SITUATION
LIKE...
THAT BRINGS TEARS TO MY EYES,
THANK YOU JONAS AND I ADMITTEDLY
ARE A BAD MARRIAGE BUT STRANGELY
WE RESPECT EACH OTHER.
I WAS SO STRUCK BY THE
PERSONALITY IT TOOK FOR HIM TO
DO THAT THAT IT BROUGHT ME TO
MILD TEARS.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, MAN.
I NEVER CRY.
SINCE HE'S DONE THAT I RESPECT
HIM EVEN MORE SO WE'RE BACK
TOGETHER AGAIN AND THAT MADE ME
FEEL REALLY REMARKABLE.
WE GOT FOUR GUYS HERE FOR SURE.
WE'RE STILL BONDD?
OKAY.
WE ALL VOTE FOR KAT.
THAT'S THE BEST WE CAN DO.
WE'LL VOTE FOR KAT.
SHE DOESN'T DO MUCH, I KNOW.
THAT'S ALL WE GOT.
SO WE'RE VOTING FOR KAT KIND
OF AS A LAST-MINUTE SCRAMBLE.
I'D RATHER VOTE MIKE OUT INSTEAD
BUT WE FIGURED, YOU KNOW, KAT,
SHE DOESN'T PULL HER WEIGHT ALL
A WHOLE LOT, SHE KIND OF ANNOYS
A LOT OF PEOPLE SO THAT'S MY
ONLY HOPE AT THIS POINT IS I'M
VOTING KAT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY CLOTHING THAT
NEEDS TO BE BOILED.
JUST MY UNDIES.
EXCELLENT.
THIS IS NOT POOP, OKAY, IT'S
DIRT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT YOU CAN SEE HOW THAT LOOKS
TO ME HOW IT COULD BE POOP,
RIGHT?
I KNOW.
I CAN'T EVEN LOOK IN THAT
DIRECTION.
I SWEAR TO GOD IT IS NOT
POOP.
IT'S CHOCOLATE, OKAY?
IT'S DIRT.
IT'S DIRT, I SWEAR.
SO WHY IS THERE DIRT
CONCENTRATED IN ONE AREA?
BECAUSE IT'S NEAR MY BUTT.
I SWEAR, IF IT'S IN BOILING
WATER YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
EVEN IF IT WAS POOP PANTS.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
WE TALKED ABOUT WHO WE
THOUGHT SHOULD GO HOME NEXT.
I WANTED TO GET A GOOD BATCH OF
LAUNDRY DONE, GET MY STUFF
CLEAN.
SO I PUT IN THE THE SALT WATER,
SCRUBBED IT REALLY GOOD WITH
SAND.
I WAS GOING TO HAVE SOME CLEAN
CLOTHES.
IT'S NOT POOP, IT'S DIRT, I
SWEAR.
YEAH, BUT I'VE ALREADY
CLEANED MY OWN IN THE OCEAN.
YOU NEED TO CLEAN THEM THE
OCEAN.
THESE HAVE BEEN CLEANED IN
THE OCEAN.
DON'T DO THAT.
LET ME CLEAN THEM IN THE
OCEAN FIRST.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT
MICROBIOLOGY.
LET ME GET MY STUFF OUT
FIRST.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY
DIFFERENCE.
I HAVE BEEN WORKING ABOUT IT.
EVEN SO THE MICROBES ARE DEAD
WHEN IT BOILS.
IT'S NOT THAT CONTAGIOUS.
I'M GOING TO GO PUKE, I'LL BE
RIGHT BACK.
YOU DON'T WANT TO TEND THE
FIRE?
IF IT WERE UP TO ME TARZAN
WOULD GO HOME BECAUSE I'M ALL
ABOUT WHO DESERVES TO BE HERE.
WHO HAS A POSITIVE ATTITUDE?
WHO BRINGS EVERYONE UP WHEN
EVERYONE'S DOWN?
WHO'S JUST A GOOD PERSON TO BE
AROUND?
TARZAN DOESN'T FILL ANY OF THOSE
EMPTY LINES.
JONAS WORKS HAS ASS OFF AND
FEEDS ALL OF US.
CAN WE SPARE HIM A COUPLE MORE
DAYS?
AND TAKE TARZAN'S ASS OUT.
AT LEAST WE HAVE SOMEONE AROUND
THAT'S FEEDING US.
TARZAN JUST PISSES EVERYONE OFF,
YOU KNOW?
I UNDERSTAND YOUR THOUGHT.
YOUR THOUGHT WAS TAKE OUT DEAD
WEIGHT.
I COMPLETELY HATE TO SEE DEAD
WEIGHT ALICIA, CHRISTINA,
TARZAN, LEIF, I HATE THEM
SITTING AROUND CAMP.
BUT YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT IT.
IF YOU SET A PLAN IN PLACE AND
IT GETS BROKEN ALL HELL CAN
BREAK LOOSE AND COME BACK TO
BITE YOU IN THE BUTT.
Jeff: SABRINA, WHAT'S THE
SINGLE-BIGGEST DIFFERENCE NOW
THAT YOU'RE MERGED AND IT IS
EVERY INDIVIDUAL FOR THEMSELVES?
IT'S VERY CHAOTIC.
EVERYONE'S TRYING TO PREDICT
WHERE THEY WILL STAND, WHO'S
WITH WHO AND JUST LIKE, OKAY, IT
CAN'T BE PEACEFUL RIGHT NOW NOT
ONE SOMEONE'S HEAD IS ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
Jeff: JONAS, IS IT
INEVITABLE TO BE THINKING "WHO
DO I WANT TO SIT NEXT TO AT THE
END AND HOW DO I MAKE SURE I'M
THERE?"
IT IS CRITICAL BUT YOU CAN BE
THINKING WAY TOO FAR AHEAD.
I HAD PEOPLE TODAY SAY "HEY,
YOU'RE A THREAT BECAUSE YOU'RE A
PROVIDER AND YOU COOK."
YEAH, BUT YOU DON'T VOTE THAT
GUY OUT FIRST!
NOT ONLY THAT, YOU WANT TO GO TO
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES AGAINST THIS
GUY?
THAT'S NOT GOOD STRATEGY.
MIKE VERSUS ME?
AS YOU CAN TELL TODAY I
DIDN'T REALLY PERFORM THAT WELL.
YOU CAN BE GREAT AT PUZZLES, I
MIGHT SUCK.
I'M NOT DONE, BRO, I'M NOT
DONE SPEAKING.
I'M PROPOSING TO THOSE PEOPLE
THAT KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT
I'M VOTING FOR MIKE TONIGHT.
WELL, MIKE, HOT SEAT BROTHER.
I DISRESPECT WHAT JONAS JUST
DID.
I DISRESPECT IT DEEPLY.
GIVING UP HIS PRINCIPLES,
THROWING MIKE UNDER THE BUS.
HE DOESN'T HAVE TO FIGHT FOR HIS
LIFE AND THAT'S THE END OF THAT.
I'M NOT GOING TO SAY ANYTHING
ELSE.
Jeff: SO, JONAS, TARZAN IS
SAYING "RELAX, BROTHER, YOU'RE
NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT."
I'M NOT SAYING THAT NOW
BECAUSE HE MAY HAVE THROWN
HIMSELF OVER THE BUS.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS
DESPITE YOUR BRILLIANT PLAN WE
DO NOT HAVE THE VOTES TO VOTE
OFF KAT.
WHAT'S I DO?
TARZAN, YOU CAN TELL ME.
IT'S OKAY.
HE'S LYING, KAT, OKAY?
IT'S GETTING WORSE AND WORSE AS
YOU GO ON, JONAS.
YOU DID PROPOSE THAT.
YOU WANT TO ATTACK ALL OF US
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT?
I'M JUST STATING THE FACT.
JEFF, I THINK WE OUGHT TO
VOTE JONAS OUT.
HE'S WORRIED ABOUT IT, WE MIGHT
AS WELL VOTE HIM OUT.
I'M SICK OF THIS.
Jeff: WHY THE BIG REACTION?
WHAT ARE WE NOT GETTING?
JONAS HAS BEEN ON MY BACK
FROM DAY ONE.
HE'S ALWAYS UNDERMINING ME.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GO UP THERE AND PUT
HIS NAME DOWN.
I'M TELLING YOU WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO.
I'M SICK OF IT, I HOPE YOU GO
HOME TONIGHT.
I'M SICK OF FIGHTING WITH YOU.
THAT'S FINE.
BUT THE BOTTOM LINE IS I'M
TRYING TO PLAY THE GAME.
YOU CAN'T BLAME ME FOR THAT.
JEFF?
Jeff: CHELSEA?
ON JONAS' DEFENSE, I THINK
MORE PEOPLE HAVE HAD ISSUES AND
ARGUMENTS WITH TARZAN THAN THEY
HAVE WITH JONAS.
Jeff: SABRINA YOU'RE
NODDING YOUR HEAD IN AGREEMENT.
I'VE HAD A COUPLE RUN-INS
WITH TARZAN LIKE EVERYONE ELSE
I'M SURE HAS BUT I HAVE HAD ZERO
ISSUES WITH JONAS.
Jeff: BUT...
THE THING IS, JEFF, IF YOU'RE
COMPARING LIKABILITY I ADMIT I'M
NOT AS LIKABLE AS JONAS.
I'M AWKWARD OUTSIDE MY
ENVIRONMENT.
Jeff: WHAT IS YOUR
ENVIRONMENT?
MY ENVIRONMENT IS A HOSPITAL
AND OPERATING ROOM AND I DO
GREAT IN THAT ENVIRONMENT.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE THE CAPTAIN OF
THE SHIP IN AN OPERATING ROOM OR
SOMEBODY DIES.
Jeff: SO THIS IS A VERY
DIFFERENT WORLD FOR YOU BECAUSE
THERE IS NO CAPTAIN OF THIS
SHIP.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE IDEAS THAT I
THINK HELP PEOPLE AND WHEN THEY
DON'T SEE IT, IT IRRITATES ME.
Jeff: SO, KIM, IT'S VERY
INTERESTING WHAT DEVELOPED HERE
TONIGHT.
YOU HAVE JONAS WHO EVERYBODY
SAYS IS LIKABLE AND PROVIDES.
HE STIRS THE POT AND OUT COMES
THE GUY ON THE END WHO SAYS "I'M
THE OLD GUY, I DON'T REALLY LIKE
THIS SOCIAL PART OF THIS
GAME...".
I DIDN'T SAY I DIDN'T LIKE
THE SOCIAL.
I SAID I'M AWKWARD IN IT.
Jeff: CASE IN POINT.
EVEN I CAN'T GET IT RIGHT.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF A MERGE,
I THINK.
YOU KNOW, ALL OF A SUDDEN PEOPLE
LIKE JONAS BECOME A THREAT AND
PEOPLE LIKE TARZAN BECOME AN
ASSET.
Jeff: DEPEND HOW YOU LOOK
AT IT.
SURE.
Jeff: CHELSEA, WHERE DO YOU
WEIGH IN ON THIS?
I JUST THINK THERE'S PEOPLE
YOU WANT TO KEEP AROUND BECAUSE
THEY'RE POSITIVE, THEY'RE
PROVIDERS, THEY HELP OUT SO MUCH
AND THEN THERE'S DEAD WEIGHT.
DID YOU MEAN ME?
MAYBE.
Jeff: SO, TARZAN, AS THIS
TRIBAL HAS EVOLVED ARE YOU
CONCERNED IT COULD BE YOU
TONIGHT?
I CAME HERE WONDERING WHETHER
ALLEGIANCES WOULD BE MAINTAINED
AND I SENSE WE'VE FALLEN APART.
SO THAT MAKES THE WHOLE THING
TOTALLY MERCURIAL AT THIS POINT
NOT KNOWING WHICH WAY OR HOW
IT'S GOING GO.
I MEAN, IF THEY WANT TO VOTE ME
OFF THAT'S FINE.
I'M VOTING FOR JONAS TONIGHT
BECAUSE OF WHAT HE DID.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S FIND
OUT HOW THIS IS GOING TO SHAKE
OUT.
YOU CAN NOT VOTE FOR TROYZAN.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS.
TIME TO VOTE.
ALICIA, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL, THE PERSON
VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JONAS.
MICHAEL.
TWO VOTES MIKE.
JONAS.
TWO VOTES MIKE; TWO VOTES JONAS.
THREE VOTES JONAS.
FOUR VOTES JONAS, TWO VOTES
MIKE.
JONAS, THAT'S FIVE VOTES JONAS,
TWO VOTES MIKE.
SIX VOTES JONAS.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY, JONAS,
THAT'S SEVEN, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
TARZAN, NO HARD FEELINGS
BROTHER.
HARD FEELINGS TO YOU.
OKAY.
Jeff: JONAS, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
HEY, GOOD LUCK WITH THAT FOOD
SITUATION.
(LAUGHS)
Jeff: WELL, YOU JUST VOTED
OUT SOMEBODY WHO ALMOST
EVERYBODY AGREES WAS LIKABLE,
WAS A PROVIDER AND WAS LOYAL.
AND THAT MEANS NOBODY IS SAFE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
SHOULD WE TALK ABOUT WHO'S
NEXT TO GO?
JAY AND TROYZAN HAVE THE
JITTERS.
HE'S A BIG THREAT AND NEEDS
TO BE TAKEN OUT A.S.A.P.
THERE'S TOO MANY GIRLS THAT
COULD START KNOCKING OUT THESE
GUYS.
Jeff: WITH GOOD REASON.
WE HAVE TO DECIDE IF WE'RE
GOING TO, LIKE, MAKE OUR MOVE
BECAUSE THIS IS NEVER GOING TO
BE THE SAME.
I'M NOT SURE HOW THIS IS ABOUT
TO GO DOWN.
SO I CAME HERE TO GO BIG OR
GO HOME AND I WENT BIG AND NOW
I'M GOING HOME.
(LAUGHS)
BUT YOU KNOW I GAVE IT ALL I GOT
AND THE FACT THAT I GOT VOTED
OUT IT KIND OF SUCKS BUT AT
LEAST... AT LEAST THEY SAID I
WAS A GOOD FISHERMAN AND A GOOD
COOK