Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON "SURVIVOR".
18 AMERICANS WERE
ABANDONED ON A REMOTE POLYNESIAN
ISLAND.
ALL WITH ONE GOAL IN MIND.
I JUST WANT TO BE THE
GREATEST SURVIVOR OF ALL TIME.
Jeff: THEY WERE QUICKLY
DIVIDED INTO TWO TRIBES-- THE
MEN VERSUS THE WOMEN.
MEN, YOUR TRIBE NAME IS MANONO.
WOMEN, YOUR TRIBE NAME IS
SALANI.
Jeff: BUT NOT EVERYONE WAS
THRILLED.
I'M THE GIRL WITHIN THE GUY
TRIBE.
Jeff: AND FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY, TWO
TRIBES FOUND THEMSELVES
COEXISTING ON ONE BEACH IN A
BATTLE OF THE SEXES.
SEEMS LIKE TOTAL CHAOS.
Jeff: ON THE SALANI TRIBE,
A GROUP OF YOUNG WOMEN WERE
RUNNING THE SHOW.
IT'S KIM, CHELSEA, KITTY KAT,
MYSELF AND A BRIE THAT AND IT
WAS DONE IN A MATTER OF SECONDS.
Jeff: AND AT MANONO, THE
MUSCLE TOOK CONTROL.
BIG MIKE, JAY-BIRD AND BILL.
I'M SITTING PRETTY AS FAR AS I'M
CONCERNED.
Jeff: A BRIE THAT THOUGHT
SHE HAD IT MADE WHEN SHE FOUND A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I FOUND THE IDOL!
Jeff: BUT ALL SHE HAD WAS A
TU DECISION TO MAKE.
IT'S FOR THE MANONO TRIBE, I
HAVE TO GIVE IT UP BEFORE THE
NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
Jeff: SABRINA GAVE IT TO
THE MAN ON THE OUTS, COLTON.
A RACE WAS CUT SHORT WHEN
KOURTNEY COULDN'T CONTINUE.
WITH KOURTNEY'S STATUS IN THE
GAME UNCERTAIN, THE WOMEN HEADED
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, THE WOMEN
IMPLODED.
YOU'RE WRONG!
OKAY?
SO SHUT UP!
Jeff: AND WHEN IT LOOKED
LIKE IT COULDN'T GET ANY WORSE,
IT DID.
LET ME GIVE YOU AN UPDATE ON
KOURTNEY.
SHE IS OUT OF THE GAME.
BUT DESPITE THE BAD NEWS, THERE
WAS A GLIMMER OF HOPE.
THE GOOD NEWS: NOBODY SELLS
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
THERE ARE 36 DAYS LEFT IN THIS
GAME AND IF YOU DON'T GET IT
TOGETHER, NONE OF YOU WILL MAKE
IT TO THE END.
17 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
GOOD EVENING, LADIES.
HI.
THE GUY SAID THAT THEY WERE
TAKING CARE OF OUR FIRE WHEN WE
WERE GONE BUT MIND YOU I AM THE
FIRE PERSON AND IF THEY WEREN'T
THERE WHEN I GOT BACK I PROBABLY
WOULD HAVE... I WOULDN'T HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO GET IT... WHOA.
WHOA!
SORRY.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE TO DO IT
MYSELF.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO VOTE
ANYBODY OUT?
NO, SHE BROKE HER WRIST IN SO
MANY DIFFERENT PLACES SHE HAS TO
HAVE SURGERY.
REALLY?
TONIGHT A COUPLE OF THE GUYS
WENT OVER TO THE WOMEN'S CAMP TO
SEE WHAT WENT ON WITH TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
KOURTNEY IS THE ONLY ONE WHO
WENT HOME.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO VOTE ANYBODY
OFF.
THEY'RE ALL SAFE AND IT'S ALL
ANNOYING.
I'M GOING TO BED.
SEE YOU GUYS IN THE MORNING.
ALICIA?
YEAH.
IS IT OKAY THAT YOU AND I CAN
TALK?
WE CAN TALK PRIVATE IF YOU WANT
OR WE CAN TALK WHEREVER YOU FEEL
COMFORTABLE.
I DON'T CARE.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
I THINK YOU AND I SHOULD
CLEAR SOME STUFF.
SURE.
TRIBAL COUNCIL COULDN'T HAVE
GONE ANY BETTER THAN I PLANNED.
THANK YOU, CHRISTINA, FOR MAKING
YOURSELF LOOK CRAZY AND TELLING
ME TO SHUT UP AND FOR ALSO
LYING.
IT ALMOST SEEMS LIKE ALL RIGHT
THEN YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ME TO
SHUT UP.
I WOULD NEVER TALK TO YOU THAT
WAY, EVER.
YOU JUST KEPT GOING ON AND ON
AND ON AND WEREN'T GIVING ME A
CHANCE TO EXPLAIN MYSELF.
I FELT LIKE TO ME THAT WAS RUDE.
OKAY.
IT WAS DISRESPECTFUL.
IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL THAN
I'M SORRY THAT I MADE YOU FEEL
THAT WAY BECAUSE THAT
WAS NOT MY INTENTION.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I MEAN, PLEASE, IF I SAW HER
SWIMMING IN AN OCEAN AND SHE WAS
DROWNING I PROBABLY WOULD LOOK
THE OTHER WAY.
(LAUGHS)
OKAY, LIKE, SERIOUSLY, DON'T
EVEN WORRY ABOUT IT.
ALL RIGHT, ARE WE GOOD?
WE'RE GOOD, GIRL, DON'T EVEN
WORRY ABOUT IT.
I HAVE MY FIVE.
KIM, KAT, CHELSEA, SABRINA AND
MYSELF SO IF IT WERE UP TO ME
AND EVERYBODY, WE WANT HER OUT.
BUT WE NEED TO WIN CHALLENGES
AND NINA LOOKS LIKE A BAG OF
ROCKS AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
THAT ANALOGY MEANS BUT SHE IS
NOT MOVING.
(LAUGHS)
IS EVERYONE HERE?
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, LADIES.
OBVIOUSLY WE JUST CAME OFF
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND IT WAS A
LITTLE FIERY BUT WE MADE IT
THROUGH.
IT'S A WASH SO LET'S GET OVER
THAT.
LET'S SET GROUND RULES AND I
THINK IT CAN GO A LOT SMOOTHER.
EVERYONE HAS A RIGHT TO BE
HEARD.
CAN I ADD SOMETHING?
HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
WHEN YOU TALK, GET TO THE POINT,
BE DIRECT.
THE QUICKER WE CAN GET THROUGH
THIS MEETING THE QUICKER WE CAN
GET TO BUSINESS AND GET THINGS
DONE HOW THIS CAMP SHOULD BE
GOING, STOCK?
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD, LIKE,
HAVE A LEADER AND SAY ALL RIGHT,
LET'S LEAVE IT UP TO HER?
I SAY SABRINA?
SAB?
BECAUSE YOU'RE JUST DIRECT,
STRAIGHT TO THE POINT, YOU DON'T
B.S.
YOU SPEAK TO US LIKE GROWN
WOMEN.
WE DON'T GET OFFENDED.
AND YOU DON'T BARK ORDERS.
FINE.
I'LL TAKE THE RESPONSIBILITY.
MANAGING THE AIR HEADS IS GOING
TO BE EXHAUSTING.
BUT HOPEFULLY WITH THIS NEW
LEADERSHIP ROLE I CAN COME IN
THERE AND JUST BE LIKE SHH.
I THINK THERE SHOULD BE THREE
CATEGORIES, WATER, FOOD, AND
SHELTER.
DOES ANYONE WANT TO BE STRAIGHT
UP ON WATER?
LIKE...
I'M WATER ALL THE TIME AND I
GOT ALL THE CANTEENS AND I'D
LIKE TO GET THEM ALL FILLED UP
TO THE GRIM IN AN HOUR.
OKAY.
GOOD.
MONICA ON WATER.
KAT AND I WILL GO SEARCHING
FOR FOOD.
IF YOU GO, SURVEY THE LAND
FIRST.
MAKE MARKERS, KNOW EXACTLY WHERE
YOU WENT.
I DON'T WANT TO OBSERVE THE
LAND.
I WANT TO GO GET STUFF.
NO, OBSERVE AND GET WHAT YOU
CAN ON THE WAY BACK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO.
AT THIS POINT IT'S DEFINITELY
THE FIVE YOUNGER GALS KIM,
CHELSEA, KAT, SAB AND ALICIA
AGAINST CHRISTINA, MONICA AND I.
AND I'VE BEEN TRYING TO FIND MY
PLACE.
I'LL NEVER TAKE FOR GRANTED
TURNING ON THE FAUCET AND
GETTING SOME WATER!
NO LUCK ON BANANAS?
I'M STILL GOING TO SEARCH IF
MY PARTNER WOULD LIKE TO GO IN
THE JUNGLE WITH ME.
SHE WAS ALL ABOUT GOING TO THE
JUNGLE.
NOW I'M GOING TO GO IN THE
JUNGLE AND FIND THE BANANAS SO
WHEN I DO FIND THE BANANAS
EVERYBODY WILL BE LIKE "OH, MY
GOD, I FOUND BANANAS."
THERE'S A DEFINITE IMMATURITY
FACTOR ON THE PART OF SOME OF
THESE WOMEN.
I LIKE KAT, I THINK SHE'S FUN.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M 51 YEARS OLD AND SHE'S
DRIVING ME NUTS!
SHE'S DRIVING ME NUTS.
I JUST WANT HER TO SHUT UP AND
WORK!
I DON'T WANT TO TIE ANY KNOTS
IF WE HAVE A CHALLENGE.
MY FINGERS HURT SO BAD.
>>S WHERE EVERYBODY?
ARE WE IN SO MUCH TROUBLE
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT DOING
ANYTHING?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
I DON'T KNOW, EITHER.
TREEMAIL!
HEY, IT SAYS "DO NOT OPEN THIS
ENVELOPE OR BOXES UNTIL MEMBERS
AND BOTH TRIBES ARE PRESENT.
BRING THE LETTER AND THE BOXES
TO A CLEARING IN A NEUTRAL
LOCATION."
WE WENT TO TREEMAIL AND THERE
WAS AN ENORMOUS BOX.
I WAS HOPING IT WAS FOOD.
ALL RIGHT, ONE... HOLD.
HOLD ON.
IT'S THIS HUGE BOX.
DOESN'T TARZAN LOOK NAKED
FROM HERE?
(LAUGHTER)
YEAH TARZAN!
FLEX THOSE MUSCLES!
TREEMAIL, Y'ALL.
READ IT.
HEAR YE, HEAR YE.
"BRING THIS ENVELOPE AND THE
BOXES TO THE CLEARING IN A
NEUTRAL LOCATION."
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
IF SOMETHING JUMPS OUT OF
THERE, I'M LIKE...
"MANONO AND SALANI YOU HAVE
BEEN COEXISTING AS TWO TRIBES
SHARING ONE WORLD.
TODAY YOUR JOURNEY WILL GO ONE
STEP FURTHER AS YOU COMPLETE A
DO IT YOURSELF REWARD CHALLENGE
HERE AT YOUR CAMP.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
YOU EACH HAVE A BOX CONTAINING A
SERIES OF KNOTTED ROPES ATTACHED
WITH A METAL RING.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO UNTIE ALL
THEIR KNOTS COMPLETELY
SEPARATING THE RING WINS THE
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
YOU ARE COMPETING TO WIN A
TARP."
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
"YOU WILL BE GETTING RAIN AND
THIS WILL SURELY KEEP YOU DRY."
THAT WILL HELP!
LOOK AT OUR ROOF.
"WHEN THE CHALLENGE IS OVER
EACH TRIBE CAN GET THEIR BOX AND
THEIR ROPES AND DO WITH IT AS
THEY SEE FIT."
(APPLAUSE)
OKAY, GUYS, OKAY.
BECAUSE WE HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON, WE'RE SITTING OUT BIG
MIKE.
HE CAN NOT PARTICIPATE
WHATSOEVER IN THIS CHALLENGE.
THE TIMING COULDN'T HAVE BEEN
BETTER.
WE'VE GOT TO GET THAT TARP.
WE NEED IT.
THE PRESSURE'S ON.
HERE'S WHERE WE CAN SHINE.
LET'S GET IT DONE.
SURVIVORS READY?
SET...
JAZZ FINGERS!
GO!
OVER THERE, OVER THERE.
PULL IT OUT THIS WAY.
PULL IT OUT TO THE FRONT.
PULL IT OUT!
EVERYBODY.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
WHEN THE CHARGE STARTS, WE
WANTED TO GET EVERYTHING OUT OF
THE BOX ON THE GROUND.
AS SOON AS THAT HAPPENS,
EVERYBODY JUST STARTED ON THE
OUTSIDE, WORKED THEIR WAY IN.
WE HAD TO JUST UNTIE
CONTINUOUSLY AND YOU FINALLY GET
TO THE MIDDLE AND THERE'S A RING
AND YOU HAVE TO UNTIE THE RING.
YOU CAN BRACE IT BETWEEN YOUR
KNEES.
WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT.
I GOT MINE OUT!
MINE ARE OUT!
OKAY, MINE'S DONE HERE.
WE NEED THIS FREAKING TARP.
GO!
EVERYBODY WAS IN A LITTLE BIT
OF A FRENZY BECAUSE WE HAD TO
GOVERN OURSELVES.
IT'S GOING TO BE RAINING HERE
VERY SOON SO THAT TARP IS THE
BIGGEST BENEFIT I THINK ANYONE
CAN HAVE.
OLD THAT ONE, HOLD THAT ONE.
THERE, THAT ONE'S OFF.
THAT ONE'S OFF.
RIGHT HERE!
PULL THAT, PULL THAT PART.
GO, GO!
I WAS SO INTO THE CHALLENGE.
THAT WAS OUR MOMENTUM AND THAT
WAS OUR SPEED AS A GROUP TO PULL
ALL THE ROPES OUT.
WE HAVE TO WIN THIS.
HOLD UP.
GUYS, SLOW DOWN.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET A BIGGER
KNOT IN ALL THIS, RIGHT?
I KNOW.
MAKE THIS COUNT.
GET THIS RIGHT HERE.
I'LL GET IT.
GO, GO, GO!
QUICK, QUICK!
COME ON, GET THIS BLUE ONE!
RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT HERE!
GO, GO.
(MEN CHEERING)
GOOD JOB.
GOOD JOB, MAN.
WE LOST THE DAMN CHALLENGE
AND THAT HURT MY SOUL!
WE NEEDED A TARP LIKE A FAT KID
NEEDS CAKE.
WE NEEDED IT.
WE WANTED IT.
WE WERE SECONDS AWAY FROM
WINNING SO IT WASN'T A HORRIBLE
LOSS BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY
IT'S A LOSS.
NO ONE EVER REMEMBERS SECOND
PLACE.
TARZAN, BRO.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA BE THERE
ALL DAY DOING THAT, DUDE.
THAT TARP IS CRITICAL.
LET'S SEE HOW BIG IT IS.
LET'S OPEN IT UP.
THIS IS A LONG BABY.
WOW!
LOOK AT THAT, MAN!
TODAY WE WON.
IT WAS LIKE IT WAS GAME ON AND
WE ALL FINISHED THE CHALLENGE.
WE WERE THE ONE THAT CAME OUT ON
TOP.
WE GOT THAT TARP WHICH WAS LIKE
THE ICING ON THE CAKE.
OUR CAMP IS GOING TO LOOK GREAT.
THE MANONO TRIBE, WE'LL HAVE THE
BEST CAMP PROBABLY IN HISTORY.
LET'S ROCK AND ROLL.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS.
PRETTY PROUD OF THIS CAMP.
DUDE, THIS IS PERFECT.
WHO BUILT THIS?
COLTON TODAY HAS DONE
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
HE'S PROVED HE'S THE WORST
PERSON FOR OUR TRIBE.
NO FIREWOOD, NO FOOD, NOTHING
WITH THE SHELTER.
HE FEELS LIKE THIS IS A
VACATION.
COLTON IS JUST HERE TO HANG OUT.
IN THE GIRL'S CAMP.
WHAT IS HE THINKING?
HE'S THE ONLY ONE NOT DOING
ANYTHING.
HE CALLS HIMSELF THE QUEEN.
YEAH, YEAH.
HE'S GOT ALL THE GIRLS IN HIS
HAND LIKE PUTTY, BRO, IF WE'RE
DOWN NUMBERS WE'RE DONE, BRO.
HE'S WORKING IT, BRO.
HE'S MAKING RUSSELL LOOK LIKE A
FREAKING LITTLE SCHOOL GIRL.
SO WE'RE JUST GOING LAYER BY
LAYER DOING TWO AT A TIME.
I'M SERIOUSLY ABOUT TO WALK
OFF THIS ISLAND.
YOU'RE NOT WALKING OFF THIS
ISLAND.
YOU'VE GOT TOO MUCH SPUNK TO
WALK OFF THE ISLAND.
YOU SHOULD TRY BONDING WITH THE
GUYS.
TRY A DIFFERENT METHOD, YOU
NEVER KNOW.
I HAVE NOTHING IN COMMON WITH
THE GUYS.
WE ALL HAVE AN EXTRA APPENDAGE,
THAT'S THE ONLY THING I HAVE IN
COMMON WITH THESE PEOPLE.
BUT GOING OVER TO THE GIRLS IS
KIND OF LIKE IT'S A RELEASE FOR
ME BECAUSE IT'S LIKE GOD, AT
LEAST I HAVE PEOPLE I CAN RELATE
TO AND TALK TO AND, YOU KNOW,
FIND COMMON GROUND WITH.
I LOVE THE GIRLS MORE THAN
ANYBODY ON THIS ISLAND.
ALL RIGHT, HE NEEDS A TIME
LIMIT OVER HERE.
COLTON, I'M GOING TO NEED YOU
TO MOVE OUT OF MY WAY.
WHERE DO YOU WANT ME TO PUT
THAT?
DID I DO THIS WRONG?
NO, WE'RE JUST... I'M
STACKING A SECOND LAYER.
SO... JUST LEAVE IT.
WE'RE GOOD.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
COLTON IS LIKE A VIRUS.
LIKE THERE SEEMS TO BE NOT A
CURE FOR HIM JUST YET.
TODAY I FOUND MYSELF WITHOUT
EVEN THINKING JUST ENTERTAINING
HIM HALF THE MORNING.
AND I'M JUST LIKE WHAT AM I
DOING?
COLTON, WHY YOU OVER HERE?
I'M OVER HERE BECAUSE I DON'T
WANT TO BE OVER THERE.
SERIOUSLY, I DON'T WANT TO TALK
GAME AT ALL.
I JUST WANT TO...
BUT WE HAVE TO HAVE LIKE A
GIRL TALK.
SORRY.
ARE YOU GUYS READY TO START?
YES.
OKAY, SORRY.
THAT'S COOL.
CAN I COME HANG OUT WITH Y'ALL
LATER?
I'LL ASK THE GIRLS.
IT'S COOL.
IT'S A JOINT DECISION AROUND
HERE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, IT'S
COOL.
OKAY.
LET'S HAVE A MEETING NOW.
I RELATE MORE TO GIRLS.
AND I GO OVER THERE AND TRY TO
HELP THEM AND THEY'RE LIKE "YOU
NEED TO GO."
AND THEY WANT TO HAVE A GIRL
MEETING SO I LITERALLY FEEL LIKE
I NEED TO FIND SOMEWHERE ON THE
ISLAND AND BUILD MY OWN LITTLE
HUT AND LIVE THERE AND BY MY OWN
LITTLE TRIBE.
BASICALLY IT'S NOT A REAL
MEETING, JUST ENOUGH TO GET HIM
OUT OF HERE.
ALL I KNOW IS DAY FOUR, I'M
JUST ABOUT... I GUESS I'M GOING
TO HAVE KEEP DIGGING DEEP AND GO
OVER THERE.
I FEEL LIKE IN ORDER FOR ME TO
MAKE A MOVE I HONESTLY BELIEVE I
HAVE TO HAVE SOME GIRLS.
THAT'S CASE IN POINT.
WE HAVE MORE ROPE HERE!
OH, HELLO.
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL OF
Y'ALL.
LIKE, I REALLY DO.
WHAT?
LIKE, I WANT EVERYONE TO HEAR ME
OKAY.
AGAIN, COLTON HAS SNAKED HIS
WAY BACK TO OUR DAMN CAMP.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE HAS MORE
ESTROGEN IN HIS BODY THAN
TESTOSTERONE BUT I SWEAR, WHAT A
DRAMA QUEEN.
WE DON'T NEED THAT ENERGY.
LIKE, GO TO YOUR CAMP.
HERE'S THE DEAL.
THE REAL RAW DEAL.
I DON'T HEAR ABOUT GAME... I
DON'T CARE ABOUT GAME, I DON'T
CARE ABOUT STRATEGY, Y'ALL CAN
ALL CALL B.S., THIS IS WHAT I'M
SAYING.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE NO ONE ON
THIS ISLAND.
NOT ONE PERSON.
LET THAT'S NOT TRUE, THOUGH.
LET HIM FINISH.
THIS ISN'T FAKE.
THIS ISN'T ARTIFICIAL.
I SWEAR TO GOD ON MY LIFE.
IF Y'ALL WOULD LET ME STAY WITH
Y'ALL I WOULD NOT TALK ABOUT
YOU, YOU, YOU.
I WILL NOT TALK TO THEM
ABOUT Y'ALL
LIKE, I SWEAR...
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S JUST
COLTON'S JUST LIKE FICKLE
CRAZINESS DRAMATIC AND NOW HE'S
CRYING.
IT'S JUST THE MORE HE COMES
OVER, THE MORE HE STARTS
BECOMING LIKE A JERK BY THE
MINUTE.
COLTON, HERE'S THE THING FROM
OUR END.
IT'S LIKE... IT'S NOT THAT WE
DON'T LOVE YOU AND DON'T WANT
YOU AROUND, BUT YOU CAN
UNDERSTAND WE ARE TWO TRIBES.
YOU FEAR FROM THE OTHER TRIBE
AND YOU'RE IN OUR CAMP HEARING
EVERYTHING WE'RE DOING AND YOU
HAVE TO BE ABLE TO UNDERSTAND
THAT THAT SEEMS LIKE A REALLY
DUMB, DUMB, DUMB MOVE ON OUR
PART.
THIS IS OUR TRIBE AND WE HAVE
TO START OWNING OUR TRIBE,
OWNING OUR THOUGHTS, OWNING OUR
ACTIONS AND OWNING WHAT THE
VISION OF WHAT WE WANT TO LOOK
LIKE LATER ON DOWN THE ROAD
WITHOUT HAVING A GUY WHO ACTS
LIKE A GIRL INVOLVED.
I MEAN, IF HE'S RUNNING THE SHOW
AND WE LOSE THIS DAMN GAME, I'M
JUST GOING TO SLIT MY WRISTS.
I'M GOING TO LIST IS MY WRISTS.
IT'S NOT AN OPTION FOR US TO
HAVE YOU OVER HERE ALL THE TIME.
I KNOW.
WE JUST CAN'T.
I'M GOING TO GET WATER.
TARZAN!
(CHANTING)
YEAH!
YEAH, BABY!
WHOO!
LOOK OUT!
TARZAN, CLASSIC.
YOU ARE A CLASSIC.
TARZAN'S, LIKE, SO CRAZY
SOMETIMES.
I WOULD NEVER TALK TO THESE
PEOPLE OUTSIDE OF THIS GAME BUT
IN "SURVIVOR" YOU HAVE TO DO
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
GOOD NIGHT, FELLAS.
LIKE, I HAVE A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND I CAN KIND OF
REGROUP AND USE THE IDOL TO MY
ADVANTAGE.
COME HERE.
WAIT A SECOND NOW.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
I'M PLAYING THIS AT THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND I'M NOT GOING HOME.
WHO GAVE YOU THAT IDOL?
THE GIRLS.
HOLY COW.
I JUST FOUND OUT SOME STUFF
TONIGHT AND IT'S LIKE MY HEART
IS POUNDING AND, YOU KNOW, I
FOUND OUT THAT COLTON HAS AN
IDOL AND WE'VE GOT TO GET RID OF
THE MUSCLE, MEANING MIKE AND
MATT.
THERE'S NO MORE TALKING ABOUT
THIS.
WE'RE SET, OKAY.
WE'RE SET.
SEE?
COLTON REACHES INTO HIS PANTS
AND HE'S GOT THIS FREAKING IDOL.
SO COLTON WENT FROM THE FIRST
GUY TO GET VOTED OUT TO NOW THE
RINGLEADER.
AND I MEAN I KNEW THE KID WAS A
FREAK OF NATURE AS FAR AS, LIKE,
THE KID IS RIDICULOUSLY SMART.
I HAVE TO MAKE MATT AND MIKE
BELIEVE I'M STILL WITH THEM
BECAUSE IF THEY GET SCARED
THEY'RE GONNA, LIKE, PULL
SOMETHING.
I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
I'M ON BOARD WITH THE TROY,
LEIF, JONAS, AND TARZAN WHICH
IS, LIKE, THE MOST RANDOM GROUP
OF PEOPLE IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
AND UNTIL I CAN GET WITH THE
GIRLS I HAVE TO ASSOCIATE MYSELF
WITH THESE MISFITS.
THEY CAN CALL THEMSELVES THE
MISFIT ALLIANCE, I'LL JUST BE
THEIR KING.
THIS IS MY WORLD, THEY SHOULD
HAVE CALLED THIS "SURVIVOR:
COLTON'S WORLD."
THIS IS IT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YEAH!
COME ON!
Jeff: FIRST THING'S FIRST,
I'LL TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, BOTH
TRIBES WILL LINE UP SIDE BY SIDE
ON A VERY NARROW BALANCE BEAM
OVER WATER.
ONE TRIBE MEMBER AT A TIME MUST
MOVE ACROSS A BALANCE BEAM AND
AROUND THE OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS.
IF YOU FALL OFF, YOU GO BACK TO
THE START.
IF YOU TOUCH TWO PEOPLE AT ONCE
YOU'VE GOT TO JUMP IN, GO BACK
TO THE START.
ONCE ONE TRIBE MEMBER REACHES
THE FINISH PLATFORM, THE NEXT
PERSON GOES.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET ALL THEIR
TRIBE MEMBERS TO THE FINISHED
PLATFORM WINS IMMUNITY, IS SAFE
FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
MEN, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON.
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
CAN NOT SIT OUT THE SAME PERSON
IN BACK-TO-BACK CHALLENGES.
WHO'S GOING TO SIT OUT?
WE'RE GOING TO SIT
AUTOTARZAN.
TARZAN'S GOING TO SIT THIS
ONE OUT.
EVERYONE ELSE, WE'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
THEN WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
BEND THOSE KNEES.
NICE AND SLOW.
Jeff: REMEMBER, YOU CAN
ONLY TOUCH ONE PERSON AT A TIME.
LEIF, LEIF, TOUCHING TWO PEOPLE,
GOT TO JUMP IN AND GO BACK.
IF YOU TOUCH TWO PEOPLE AT ONCE
THE PERSON CROSSING HAS TO JUMP
IN AND START OVER.
SO BE CAREFUL.
DON'T GRAB ME.
Jeff: EVEN INCIDENTAL CAN
COST YOU.
SHE'S GOT THESE BIG OLD BOBS,
I CAN'T GET PAST.
Jeff: LEIF MAKING HIS WAY
PAST COLTON.
JUST LET ME GO.
Jeff: KAT AND MONICA DOING
A LITTLE DANCE.
STARTING TO FIGURE IT OUT.
LEIF STARTING TO MAKE A LITTLE
PROGRESS NOW.
KEEP DOING WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
Jeff: TAKES A LOT OF
COMMUNICATION.
KAT WORKING PAST CHELSEA.
REACH AROUND WITH YOUR ARMS,
THAT'S WHAT I DID.
YOU'RE PUSHING ME BACKWARDS,
WHICH IS NOT GOOD.
GOT ME?
I GOT YOU.
Jeff: LEIF MAKING HIS WAY
PAST HALF OF HIS TRIBE NOW.
HE'S GOT A STRATEGY GOING AND
IT'S WORKING.
ALL RIGHT, LEIF, COME ON.
Jeff: LEIF MAKING HIS WAY
PAST JAY NOW.
KAT STILL STUCK AT CHELSEA.
MONICA, DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
DO THIS BETTER?
KEEP GOING.
COME ON, GUYS, MAKE A MOVE.
Jeff: THE WOMEN MAKE
NOTHING PROGRESS.
WE'RE IN THE LEAD.
Jeff: LEIF VERY CLOSE TO
THE END.
LEIF TO THE FINISHED PLATFORM.
MEN HAVE THEIR FIRST PERSON
ACROSS.
NOW COLTON STARTS THE WALK.
KAT NOW GOING BEHIND CHELSEA.
GOING TO TRY A DIFFERENT
STRATEGY.
KAT KNOWS SHE'S GOT TO PICK UP
THE PACE NOW.
GO BEHIND REAL QUICK.
HOLD ME HOLD ME!
I GOT YOU!
Jeff: NO, NO, NO!
CHRISTINA REACHED OUT AND
GRABBED KAT, KIM FALLS IN, KAT'S
GOT TO GO IN, SHE TOUCHED TWO
PEOPLE.
WOMEN ARE STARTING OVER.
HOLD ME.
LIKE, HOLD ME.
Jeff: COLTON WORKING
AROUND...
DON'T DROP ME.
Jeff: KAT MAKING HER WAY
AROUND KIM NOW.
COLTON GETTING VERY CLOSE TO THE
END.
COLTON, STOP, STOP.
GIVE MIKE SOME MORE SPACE.
NO, WE NEED TO GIVE MIKE A
LITTLE MORE SPACE.
I WISH HE'D SHUT UP.
LEIF, WE'RE GOOD.
CHILL OUT.
HOLD ME HOLD ME.
I GOT YOU.
Jeff: COLTON AND MATT, NICE
RECOVERY.
NICE BALANCE.
STAY.
I'M GOING TO FALL.
NO, I'M NOT.
YOU'RE NOT.
Jeff: CHRISTINA, YOU TOUCHED
TWO.
KAT, IN THE WATER.
WHAT?
Jeff: KAT, CHRISTINA IS
TOUCHING TWO PEOPLE.
GET IN AND GO.
GO, GO.
Jeff: MAKE SURE YOU DO NOT
TOUCH TWO PEOPLE AT ONCE!
WRAP YOUR ARM AROUND ME!
Jeff: MICHAEL GIVING COLTON
A BIG HUG AND THAT WILL DO IT.
COLTON MAKES IT TO THE END.
THE MEN HAVE TWO ACROSS.
WOMEN STILL WORKING ON THEIR
FIRST.
HOLD ME, PULL ME BACK.
I NEED TO GO FURTHER BACK.
Jeff: KAT MAY HAVE NOT BEEN
THE BEST PERSON TO PUT ON THE
END.
SHE HAS THE FURTHEST ROUTE TO
GO.
JONAS GETS AROUND JAY MAKING
QUICK WORK OF THIS.
KAT NOW BACK AT CHRISTINA.
AND WITH THAT, CHRISTINA'S IN
THE WATER.
I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE TO GO
BACK...
Jeff: KAT JUST JUMPS BACK
IN.
KAT, YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
BACK IN, BABE.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
YOU GOT IT, YEAH!
Jeff: JONAS GETS AROUND
MICHAEL.
MEN HAVE THEIR THIRD PERSON TO
THE FINISH PLATFORM.
BILL NOW STARTS HIS WALK.
GET CHRISTINE ONE TIME.
IF IT DOESN'T WORK I'LL GO.
I'LL DO IT ALL.
I'D LOVE TO.
YOU FEEL ME?
YOU'RE FINE.
Jeff: BILL FALLS IN.
JAY GOES IN.
A SETBACK FOR THE MEN.
MAYBE AN OPENING FOR THE WOMEN
IF THEY CAN PICK UP THE PACE.
COME CON!
Jeff: AND CHRISTINA'S IN
THE WATER ONCE AGAIN.
MONICA'S GOING.
MONICA JUMPS IN, SHE'S GOING
TO PUT HERSELF AT THE END.
BILL MAKES HIS WAY ONCE AGAIN
AROUND TROYZAN.
MONICA TRYING TO GET AROUND
CHRISTINA.
TWO HANDS.
KAT REACHED OUT AND GRABBED YOU,
MONICA YOU'VE GOT TO GO IN, TOO.
OH, KAT, YOU'RE ABOUT AS DUMB
AS A ROCK.
ONCE AGAIN KAT JUMPED IN FOR
NO REASON.
WOMEN COMPLETELY FALLING APART.
MEANWHILE, THE MEN ARE MAKING
QUICK WORK OF THIS.
BILL ACROSS.
THE MEN NOW HAVE FOUR AT THE
FINISH PLATFORM.
HOLD ME, SWIM ME OVER.
Jeff: MONICA GETS PAST
CHRISTINA.
JAY WORKING HIMSELF AROUND MATT.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU GOT THIS.
COME ON, Y'ALL!
PUSH ME AROUND!
I CAN STAY STRONG IN THE CORE.
Jeff: MONICA FINALLY
GETTING SOMETHING GOING.
MONICA NOW PAST KIM.
JAY IS NOW THROUGH MIKE.
JAY IS NOW ON THE FINISHED
PLATFORM.
THE MEN HAVE ONLY THREE LEFT.
HOLD ME, GUIDE ME OVER.
I'M STRONG.
Jeff: MONICA GETS PAST
CHELSEA.
THE WOMEN HAVE SOMETHING GOING.
IS IT TOO LITTLE TOO LATE?
I LOVE YOU.
COME ON, TRY!
Jeff: TROY AND MICHAEL FALL
OFF.
ONCE AGAIN AN OPENING FOR THE
WOMEN.
MONICA MAKES HER WAY AROUND
ALICIA.
GUIDE ME AROUND.
LIFT ME UP.
MONICA NOW PAST THE GREEN AND
THE WOMEN HAVE THEIR FIRST
PERSON.
CHRISTINA NOW GIVING IT A GO.
ALL THE WAY AROUND!
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: TROY IS AROUND
MICHAEL.
CHRISTINA TRYING TO GET AROUND
KIM NOW.
TROY GETS AROUND MATT WITH NO
PROBLEM.
THIS IS IT.
MIKE HAS TO GET AROUND MATT AND
THIS CHALLENGE IS OVER.
THE WOMEN TRYING TO COME BACK.
BUT IT WILL BE TOO LITTLE; TOO
LATE IN THIS CHALLENGE.
MATT LEAD HIM BACK.
CAN HE HOLD ON?
AND HE DOES.
MIKE WILL CROSS AND MATT
CROSSES.
MEN WIN IMMUNITY!
(SCREAMING)
MEN, COME ON OVER AND GRAB IT.
GOOD JOB, MONICA.
YES!
Jeff: CONGRATULATIONS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
THANK GOD!
IT'S DEFINITELY THE BOOBS ARE
HARD.
Jeff: HARD TO SEE THEM WALK
OFF WITH IMMUNITY AGAIN.
NINA, YOU'RE SHAKING YOUR HEAD
IN DISGUST.
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT'S BEEN
GOING FOR US THIS WHOLE LAST
FIVE DAYS.
NO COMMUNICATION, NO TEAM WORK.
SAME OLD STORY.
WELL, THE RESULT IS THE SAME.
TRIBAL COUNCIL AGAIN TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS TRIBE.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
KAT JUMPED IN WHEN SHE DIDN'T
EVEN NEED TO JUMP IN-- NOT ONCE,
TWICE.
I'M SAD.
I'M SAD FOR WOMEN.
THIS ISN'T THE WAY WOMEN ARE AND
FRANKLY I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
ALL RIGHT.
UM... EVERYBODY WANTS TO SAY
SOMETHING.
WHOEVER WANTS TO START.
I'M SORRY FOR HAVING HORRIBLE
COMMUNICATION SKILLS.
I THOUGHT I COULD DO IT BUT IT
WAS SO HARD.
IT REALLY WAS.
YOU GAVE IT A GOOD SHOT AND
IT WAS HARD.
I REALLY WANTED TO DO IT.
KAT, I ALWAYS THINK OF YOU AS
A LITTLE CRACKER JACK, SO IT'S
OKAY.
I ALWAYS STEP UP IN THE THAT
ROLE REGARDLESS OF IF I'M
ATHLETIC OR NOT BECAUSE I FEEL
LIKE I ALWAYS WANT TO BRING IT.
I ALWAYS WANT TO BRING THE TRIBE
TO NUMBER ONE YOU KNOW?
THAT'S WHAT I ALWAYS WANT.
YOU'RE VERY MUCH OF A RAH-RAH
GIRL AND WE NEED THAT.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY LOGIC
AND STRATEGY TRUMPS RAH-RAH.
SO DO THAT ON THE INSIDE AND
LISTEN FOR STRATEGY.
KAT, I REALLY LIKE HER ENERGY,
BUT IT NEEDS TO BE CHANNELED.
WE WANT TO TRY TO KEEP THINGS
CONTROLLED AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE--
AT LEAST I DO IF I'M BEING THE
LEADER-- AND KAT IS VERY YOUNG
AND EMOTIONAL.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH BEING
EMOTIONAL IF YOU CAN CONTROL IT
BUT SHE CAN'T CONTROL IT AT ALL
AND THAT'S A LIABILITY.
HOWEVER, NINA IS LIKE THE
WALKING DEAD AROUND HERE.
SHE KNOWS HER HEAD IS ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE TO THINK IT
WAS ONE PERSON'S FAULT TODAY AT
ALL BECAUSE THAT REALLY WASN'T
THE CASE.
BUT TONIGHT'S GOING TO END LIKE
THE OTHER NIGHTS, IN TRIBAL
COUNCIL, SO THAT'S THE SUCKY
PART.
WE DIDN'T LOSE, WE GOT OUR
ASS KICKED.
IT WASN'T EVEN CLOSE AND
EVERYONE'S LIKE "OH, KAT, YOU
DID SO GOOD."
KAT, YOU JUMPED IN THE WATER
TWICE, YOU DUMB BLOND!
TWICE!
INEXCUSABLE.
COME ON!
QUIT BEING SUCH A DUMB BROAD!
WE'RE NOT GOING TO SURVIVE.
I'M SORRY...
IT'S ME, YOU AND CHRISTINA.
WE'RE OUT.
I DON'T THINK WE'RE GOING TO
MAKE IT OUT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT ORDER.
ME, YOU AND CHRISTINA ARE OUT OF
HERE.
I'M VOTING FOR KAT BECAUSE I
CAN'T STAND HER.
I THINK SHE'S A COMPLETE IDIOT.
NOT ONCE JUMPING IN THE WATER AT
THE WRONG TIME, TWICE.
IT'S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE, KAT.
IT'S JUST...
I'M SO LOW ON THE TOTEM POLE,
HOW DO I POSSIBLY GO TO SOMEBODY
IN THE FIVE AND SAY "WOULD YOU
GUYS BE INTERESTED IN GETTING
RID OF KAT"?
THAT'S A ONE-WAY TICKET HOME.
SO I'M HOPING THEY'LL OPEN THEIR
EYES BUT WHO KNOWS WITH THIS
GROUP.
WHO KNOWS?
WE ARE IN A TRIBE OF THE IT
WITH IT WITHLESS.
WE ARE A WITHLESS TRIBE AND WE
ARE BEING LED BY 20
SOMETHING-YEAR-OLD WOMEN AND
THEY ARE...
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
AND I HAVE TO HEAR KAT RUN
HER MOUTH ONE MORE TIME... THAT
DUMBER THAN DUMB...
SHE SHOULD BE GOING TONIGHT.
IT SUCKS.
IT DOES.
IT'S ONLY GOING TO GET WORSE.
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
OH, MY GOSH, KAT!
SHE SHOULD BE GOING HOME.
SHE'S BEEN REALLY RUINING THIS
TRIBE.
I KNOW SHE'S FUN BUT SHE'S
RUINING IT.
IGNORANT.
OUT LAST, OUT WITH, BUT YOU
CAN'T WHEN YOU'RE IT HAVELESS.
YOU'RE TOO SMART TO LET THIS
HAPPEN.
WE CAN REDEEM OURSELVES BECAUSE
RIGHT NOW WE LOOK LIKE IDIOTS.
TRUST ME, I'VE BEEN
EMBARRASSED SINCE I'VE BEEN
HERE.
LET'S FIX IT!
I'M WRITING DOWN KAT'S NAME.
I WAS GOING TO ANYWAY.
I JUST TALKED TO NINA, OF
COURSE.
SHE... I MEAN... SHE'S REALLY...
I MEAN, SHE'S REALLY RIGHT ABOUT
KAT.
KAT MAKES US ALL OUT TO BE
FREAKING IDIOTS.
AND I KNOW WE NEED TO FOCUS ON
NUMBERS, BUT WHAT IF... IF WE
VOTED KAT OUT.
ALL EYES ARE ON KAT RIGHT
NOW.
WE'RE STARTING TO LOOK AT THE
WEAKER PLAYERS EVEN IF THEY'RE
IN OUR ALLIANCE.
I'M ONE OF THE STRONGEST PEOPLE
IN THE TRIBE SO IF WE DECIDE TO
START PICKING OFF THE WEAKEST
LINKS, KAT WILL BE OUR PICK.
IT KILLS ME TO TALK TO NINA
BECAUSE I UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING
SHE'S SAYING.
I DO, TOO.
AND I KNOW KAT BLEW THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
I'M TOTALLY WITH YOU ON THAT.
I JUST FEEL NINA DESERVES TO BE
HERE MORE THAN KAT.
I'M WITH YOU SO I'M
RESPECTING YOU IN THIS IDEA.
I JUST THINK WE NEED THESE GIRLS
TO TRUST US.
I DON'T KNOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GIVE TONIGHT'S TRIBAL SOME
CONTEXT.
WE'RE ONLY FIVE DAYS IN BUT
YOU'RE OFF TO ONE OF THE WORST
STARTS EVER IN THIS GAME BECAUSE
OF THE ABSOLUTE AND TOTAL
DYSFUNCTION WITHIN THIS GROUP.
KIM, WHAT DO YOU BRING INTO THIS
GAME?
WHAT COULD HELP RIGHT NOW FROM
YOUR LIFE?
I THINK I'M A GOOD
COMMUNICATOR AND I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WE NEED.
BUT I DON'T THINK THERE'S A
PLACE FOR MY VOICE YET.
Jeff: IT'S ALMOST LIKE I'M
TALKING TO SIXTH GRADERS SAYING
"HEY, EVERYBODY, IF YOU HAD A
GROUP OF PEOPLE AND YOU HAD TO
FIGURE SOMETHING OUT, WHAT MIGHT
BE ONE THING YOU WOULD DO?"
AND SOMEBODY SAYS "WE COULD TALK
ABOUT WHAT WE KNOW."
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS HASN'T
HAPPENED YET, NINA.
WELL, UNFORTUNATELY, A LOT OF
THAT INFORMATION ABOUT ALL OF US
DOESN'T GET OUT BECAUSE WE'RE
STILL A DIVIDED TRIBE.
THERE'S FIVE AGAINST THREE.
Jeff: WHO ARE THE FIVE.
SABRINA, CHELSEA, ALICIA, KAT
AND KIM.
Jeff: AND THAT LEAVES YOU,
NINA, WITH CHRISTINA AND MONICA?
CORRECT.
Jeff: WELL, DOES EVERYONE
HERE KNOW, FOR INSTANCE, ABOUT
YOUR BACKGROUND?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I HAVE SHARED
WITH SOME MEMBERS OF THIS TRIBE
MY LIFE EXPERIENCE.
I WAS A POLICE OFFICER FOR THE
CITY OF LOS ANGELES FOR 13
YEARS.
WITH THAT BRINGS THE ABILITY TO
DEAL UNDER PRESSURE AND TO BE
PHYSICAL SO I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHAT LIFE
EXPERIENCE KAT BRINGS TO THIS
GROUP.
Jeff: KAT?
I MEAN, I'M OUT DOORS AND I
DO SALES AND I WORK WITH PEOPLE
ALL THE TIME AND, UM,...
Jeff: IT WOULDN'T BE
UNREASONABLE OF YOU, KAT, TO SAY
"I'M YOUNG, MY LIFE EXPERIENCE
IS LIMITED."
OF COURSE, I'VE NEVER DONE
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
I'M YOUNG, THIS IS A NEW
EXPERIENCE FOR ME, PERIOD.
I'M THE YOUNGEST PERSON ON
THE TRIBE.
AND I'M OLD.
I'VE NEVER DONE THIS, EITHER.
OKAY, I'M THE YOUNGEST PERSON
ON THIS TRIBE AND I'M DOING THE
BEST I CAN.
EVEN TODAY, LIKE, WITH OUR
CHALLENGE I WAS SO EXCITED AND
THE WORST FEELING IN THE WHOLE
WORLD IS TO LET YOUR TRIBE DOWN.
AND I DID.
TODAY.
Jeff: NINA YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE ABOUT TO BURST SO MUCH IS
READY TO COME OUT.
WELL, KAT IS ALWAYS TELLING
US WHAT A GREAT ATHLETE SHE IS.
BUT AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED
ATHLETE IS MADE UP OF THREE
THINGS: ATHLETIC ABILITY, THE
ABILITY TO HANDLE PRESSURE AND
TO BE SMART.
OKAY, SO TODAY NOT ONLY DID SHE
JUMP IN THE WATER ONCE, SHE DID
IT TWICE.
AND THE ONLY VOICE I HEARD UP
THERE, DISTRACTING VOICE, WAS
HERS.
SO SHE CAN'T HANDLE STRESS AND
SHE MADE A MISTAKE.
IS SHE AN ATHLETE?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT THERE'S THREE COMPONENTS AND
SHE'S FAILED AT TWO.
Jeff: KIM, IS PART OF
WHAT'S GOING ON THAT THERE'S AN
ALLIANCE FORMED?
I THINK THAT'S PART OF IT.
DOES KAT BRING LIFE EXPERIENCE
TO THE TABLE IN OUR TRIBE?
NO.
BUT I DO THINK KAT IS A GOOD
ATHLETE.
DO I THINK NINA HAS LIFE
EXPERIENCE?
ABSOLUTELY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, SHE'S BRINGING
DIFFERENT THINGS TO THE TABLE
THAN KAT IS AND THAT'S THE
DECISION WE'RE WEIGHING OUT HERE
TONIGHT.
Jeff: SO IT'S BETWEEN NINA
AND KAT.
THAT'S BEEN THE VIBE TODAY.
Jeff: CHELSEA, IF YOU COULD
START OVER, DO YOU THINK YOU
GUYS WOULD FORM DIFFERENT
ALLIANCES.
YEAH, IT WOULD PROBABLY BE
DIFFERENT.
Jeff: SABRINA, DO YOU AGREE
WITH THAT?
YES, 100%.
Jeff: ALICIA, THERE'S NO
GIRL POWER GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
NO YOUNG WOMEN AT HOME GOING "GO
WOMEN'S TRIBE!"
NO, THERE'S NOT.
Jeff: IS THAT EMBARRASSING?
IT'S VERY EMBARRASSING,
ESPECIALLY THAT CHALLENGE.
MONICA FIGURED IT OUT BUT
BECAUSE EVERYBODY WAS TALKING WE
COULDN'T HEAR MONICA'S
SUGGESTION.
AND IT WAS EMBARRASSING TO
WATCH.
MY FAULT.
IT WAS MY FAULT.
Jeff: YOU KEEP SAYING THAT.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT OR ARE YOU
JUST BEING A MARTER?
I THINK I DO.
IT SUCKS.
Jeff: WHAT'S UPSETTING?
MY COMMUNICATION SKILLS, I
GUESS.
AND FAILING.
I NEVER FAIL.
Jeff: YOU'VE NEVER FAILED
AT ANYTHING IN LIFE?
I USUALLY DON'T TRY ANYTHING
UNLESS I KNOW I'M GOING TO
SUCCEED, PUT IT THAT WAY.
Jeff: SO YOU REALLY CAN'T
SAY YOU'VE NEVER FAILED BECAUSE
THE TRUTH IS YOU'VE NEVER PUT
YOURSELF IN A POSITION TO FAIL.
YEAH.
IT HURTS.
Jeff: SO, KAT, YOU SAID YOU
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE
LOSS.
WOULD IT BE FAIR TO VOTE YOU
OUT?
ABSOLUTELY.
I THOUGHT I COULD DO IT.
I THOUGHT I COULD BRING IT HOME.
WHAT I CAN ONLY HOPE IS THAT MY
TRIBE BELIEVES IN ME THE WAY
THAT I BELIEVE IN MYSELF AND
THEY'LL KEEP ME AROUND SO I CAN
SHOW THEM THAT I'M LEARNING.
YOU KNOW?
I'M NOT CALLING CHRISTINA OUT
BUT THERE ARE PEOPLE IF THAT, IF
ANYTHING, COULD BE HERE TO JUST
BE HERE AS OPPOSED TO PLAY THE
GAME.
Jeff: CHRISTINA, SHE JUST
THREE YOU UNDER THE BUS.
YOU KNOW, YOU TAKE IT IN AND
YOU MOVE ON.
CAN I JUST JUMP IN IF?
SEE, THIS IS A PRIME EXAMPLE OF
HOW MEN AND WOMEN COMMUNICATE
DIFFERENTLY.
WE'RE KIND OF TIPTOEING AND TAP
DANCING AROUND AND THAT CAUSES A
RIFT AND IT CAUSES EMOTION.
I MAN WOULD HAVE CALLED ANOTHER
MAN OUT AND THEY WOULD HAVE
DEALT WITH IT AND BE DONE WITH
IT, NO MANY "B."
Jeff: NINA, DOES THIS GIVE
YOU A FEELING OF HOPE HEARING
THAT WELL, NOW HERE'S CHRISTINA,
SOMEBODY ELSE YOU SHOULD GET RID
OF BEFORE ME.
SHE DOESN'T EVEN WANT TO PLAY
THE GAME.
ABSOLUTELY.
BECAUSE I DO BRING LIFE
EXPERIENCE, I AM PHYSICAL AND I
HAVE PLENTY OF ENERGY.
AND THEY KNOW THAT.
Jeff: WITH THAT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
MONICA, YOU'RE UP.
NINA, I THINK YOU'RE A STRONG
COMPETITOR BUT I WOULD NEVER
THROW YOU UNDER THE BUS THE WAY
YOU DID ME.
KAT, I'VE ALREADY SAID MY
REASONS WHY YOU SHOULD GO HOME.
THERE'S BEEN ENOUGH SHENANIGANS
AROUND CAMP AND IT'S JUST TIME
FOR YOU TO LEAVE.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, NINA.
KAT.
CHRISTINA.
ONE VOTE NINA, ONE VOTE KAT, ONE
VOTE CHRISTINA.
NINA.
TWO VOTES NINA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES NINA.
ONE VOTE KAT, ONE VOTE
CHRISTINA.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: ONE WORLD," NINA.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
NINA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, WE ARE ONLY FIVE DAYS IN,
BUT YOU'RE TWO TRIBE MEMBERS
DOWN AND YOU'VE YET TO WIN A
CHALLENGE.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET IT TOGETHER.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions and CBS.
Captioned by Media Access Group
at WGBH access.wgbh.org