Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
FOR THE FIRST FIVE DAYS, THE
MEN'S TRIBE WAS ON A ROLL,
DOMINATING EVERY CHALLENGE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
EVEN THOUGH THIS IS ONE
WORLD, AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
WE HERE IN CHARGE OF THIS GAME.
Jeff: LEAVING THE WOMEN OF
SALANI HANGING ON BY A THREAD.
IS THERE ANY WAY WE COULD
POSSIBLY HAVE AN EMBER?
I'M SORRY, I'M A REPUBLICAN,
I DO NOT BELIEVE IN HANDOUTS.
Jeff: BUT THE WOMEN
WEATHERED THE STORM WITH
BACK-TO-BACK VICTORIES.
THE WOMEN WIN IMMUNITY!
THINGS ARE STARTING TO FEEL
DIFFERENT.
Jeff: BUT EVEN REWARDS AND
SUNSHINE COULDN'T KEEP THEM FROM
EACH OTHER'S THROATS.
WHAT IS IT GOING TO TAKE TO
WORK TOGETHER?
IT'S GUYS VERSUS GIRLS AND
CHRISTINA IS PLAYING THAT SIDE
AND PLAYING US AT THE SAME TIME.
SHE'S POISON.
Jeff: FACING THEIR FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, THE MISMISFIGHT
ALLIANCE TARGETED MAT, THE HEAD
OF THE MUSCLE ALLIANCE.
BUT COLTON WAS HARBOR AGO
PERSONAL VENDETTA AND WANTED TO
TAKE OUT BILL.
BILL IS THE TYPE THAT WILL
SLIT UP BEHIND YOU AND SLIT YOUR
THROAT.
WE KNOW THAT.
SO YOU NEED TO ELIMINATE THAT
FIRST.
YOU'RE GUTTER TRASH, THAT'S
ALL YOU ARE.
I CAN'T STAND HIM.
UGH!
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THE MISFIT ALLIANCE DECIDED MAT
WAS A BIGGER THREAT AND HE WAS
SENT HOME.
TIME FOR YOU GO.
FIRST VOTE, FIRST BLIND SIDE,
GAME ON.
15 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
.
GETTING BACK FROM TRIBAL IS
LITTLE UPSETTING BECAUSE MATT
WENT HOME.
THESE GUYS DON'T KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE DOING.
MOST OF THOSE GUYS ARE WEAK AND
THEY WANT TO KEEP THE WEAK GUYS
AROUND.
YOU HAVE THE OLD GUY, YOU HAVE
TO LITTLE GUY, OFF GAY GUY WHO
DOESN'T WANT TO WORK.
IF THEY WANT TO VOTE OUT THE
STRONG GUYS THEY CAN CONTINUE TO
LOSE
LOSE.
THAT WENT WELL.
YEAH.
HERE'S THE THING REAL
QUICKLY.
MIKE IS SO PERIPHERAL, HE HAS NO
CLUE.
WE CAN LET HIM FLOAT A LITTLE
BIT BEFORE WE VOTE HIM OUT.
IT WAS GOOD FOR US THAT WE HAD
TO GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE
I TRULY FELT THE FIVE OF US WERE
SOLID.
THE FIVE ARE MYSELF AND TROYZAN,
JONAS, COLTON AND LEE.
WE STAND SOLID AT THE MOMENT FOR
AT LEAST THE FIRST ROUND.
SO THE NEXT GUY IS BILLY,
BECAUSE HE'S THE ONE MOST LIKELY
TO PULL SOMEBODY AWAY FROM US.
GOOD CALL.
BILL'S VERY DANGEROUS.
HE'S CAPABLE OF LOOSENING THE
TIES THAT BIND US FIVE WITH HIS
CHARM, HIS BEGUILING CHARACTER.
HE'S A SMART COOKIE.
YEAH, AND HE'S DANGEROUS.
OH, YEAH, I BELIEVE THAT.
SO TOMORROW WE'RE SOLIDIFY
THAT IDEA.
OKAY.
GOOD MORNING!
ARE YOU EXCITING LOOKING AT
YOUR GOOD HEARTY BREAKFAST?
OOH.
GOOD OLD SNAILS FOR
BREAKFAST.
THE WOMEN HAVE HAD A HUGE
TURNAROUND.
WE WON THE LAST TWO CHALLENGES
AND WE'RE NOT STARVING.
I MEAN, REALLY AND TRULY BETWEEN
COCONUT, SNAILS, AND THE RICE,
WE REALLY COULD PROBABLY GO ON
FOR 31 MORE DAYS.
I MEAN, I COULD.
IT'S MIND OVER MATTER.
NICE.
WE'RE PRETTY
SOPHISTICATED.
OKAY, SO DID YOU GUYS USE
THAT NET YET?
YEAH, WE TRIED TO USE IT
YESTERDAY.
IF YOU GUYS WANT... I'M FROM
HAWAII.
I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW, I'VE
USED A NET BEFORE AND I KNOW
EXACTLY WHERE TO LAY IT AND WHEN
TO LAY IT AND HOW LONG TO LAY
IT.
SO HERE'S WHAT WE'RE
PROPOSING.
IF WE COULD USE THE NET WE'RE
WILLING TO GIVE YOU HALF OF IT.
ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
I JUST THINK IT'S HILARIOUS AT
THE BEGINNING IT WAS US
STRUGGLING AND NOW THE BOYS COME
BY WANTING EVERYTHING WE WIN IN
CHALLENGES.
IT'S JUST CRAZY HOW MUCH THE
ROLES HAVE REVERSED IN NINE
DAYS.
I KNOW I PROBABLY SOUND LIKE
A COLDHEARTED BITCH AND I'M NOT.
BUT WE CAN'T BE FEEDING OUR
ENEMIES.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO DO IT,
WE'RE FINE WITH THAT.
WE'RE GETTING ENOUGH FOOD AS IT
IS.
BUT IT WOULD BE A LOT EASIER FOR
BOTH OF US.
THINK ABOUT IT, WE'RE DOING ALL
THE WORK AND YOU'RE GETTING HALF
OF IT?
I DON'T REALLY CARE EITHER WAY.
YOU DON'T CARE EITHER WAY?
I THINK JONAS IS A REAL RUDE
DUDE.
HE MADE THE OFFER WITH THE NET
AND THEN KEPT SAYING "I MEAN, I
DON'T CARE.
I DON'T CARE.
I DON'T CARE."
BUT OBVIOUSLY HE CARES A LOT.
IT WOULD JUST BE A LOT EASIER
FOR BOTH OF US.
YOU GUYS CAN THINK ABOUT THAT
AND GET BACK TO US.
THE WOMEN, THEY'RE TRYING TO
BE SUCH HARD-NOSES, I DON'T GET
THAT.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEIR EMOTIONS
ARE TURNING THEM WHACKY OR WHAT
BUT THEY'RE EMOTIONAL CREATURES
AND THEY CAN'T SEEM TO THINK
STRAIGHT.
DON'T THINK I'M A BITCH!
WELL, YOU JUST MADE A BITCH
MOVE.
SO THEY'RE DOING NOTHING.
THEY CAN SUN TAN ON THE BEACH
WHILE WE GO FISH AND BRING THEM
HALF OF THE FOOD.
(LAUGHS)
LIKE, HELLO?
IS ANYBODY HOME?
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
YES, SIR!
Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU WILL TAKE TURNS USING A
SLINGSHOT TO FIRE COCONUTS AT A
MASSIVE WALL OF TARGETS.
FORD FOR IT TO COUNT, YOU HAVE
TO KNOCK OUT THE MAJORITY OF THE
TARGET.
FIRST TRIBE TO KNOCK OUT FIVE
TARGETS IN A ROW EITHER HORIZON
VERTICAL OR DIAGONAL
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
YES.
Jeff: THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL HAVE A CHOICE BETWEEN ONE
OF THREE REWARDS.
YOU CAN CHOOSE COMFORT.
OH!
Jeff: PILLOWS, BLANKETS AND
A MATTRESS.
A MATTRESS!
Jeff: OR YOU CAN CHOOSE
PROTECTION FOR FROM THE RAIN.
WE HAVE THAT.
Jeff: THE FORM OF A TARP.
MEN ALREADY HAVE ONE.
OR IF EVERYTHING'S GOING REALLY
WELL AND YOU DON'T NEED EITHER
OF THOSE.
YOU CAN TAKE SOME LUXURY.
OH, MY GOD!
DOUGHNUTS!
Jeff: COFFEE, SUGAR,
CREAMER AND A HUGE PLATEFUL OF
DOUGHNUTS TO TAKE BACK TO CAMP.
I CAN TELL IT'S WORTH PLAYING
FOR.
MEN, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE.
I'LL SIT IT.
BILL IS GOING TO SIT THIS ONE
OUT, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
COLTON UP FOR THE MEN.
KILL IT, COLTON.
Jeff: MONICA UP FOR THE
WOMEN.
YOU'RE LOOKING TO CONNECT FIVE
IN A ROW.
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
COLTON CONNECTS BUT DOESN'T
KNOCK IT OUT.
MONICA KNOCKS OUT A COUPLE OF
PLANKS BUT NOT QUITE ENOUGH.
THOSE ARE NOT HITS.
WE'RE STILL EVEN, ZIP-ZIP.
NEXT TWO.
SABRINA NOW FIRING FOR THE
WOMEN.
TARZAN UP FOR THE MEN.
COME ON, TARZAN!
DOUGHNUTS, DOUGHNUTS!
Jeff: MEN TALKING NOTHING
BUT DOUGHNUTS OVER HERE.
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
SABRINA CONNECTS BUT NOT ENOUGH.
TARZAN CONNECTS FOR THE MEN!
THE MEN ARE ON THE BOARD WITH
ONE!
NEXT TWO.
KAT FOR THE WOMEN, TROYZAN FOR
THE MEN.
MEN CONNECT BUT NOT ENOUGH KAT
CONNECTS FOR THE WOMEN!
THE WOMEN ARE ON THE BOARD WITH
THEIR FIRST POINT.
YEAH!
LIKE THAT?
SMELL THAT?
Jeff: NEXT TWO, WE ARE 1-1,
BUT THE KEY IS GETTING FIVE IN A
ROW.
ALL THE WAY, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
Jeff: LISA GOING WAY BACK.
OH!
Jeff: MICHAEL CONNECTS FOR
THE MEN AND KNOCK OUT THEIR
SECOND TARGET.
NEXT TWO.
LEIF FOR THE MEN, KIM READY TO
TAKE A SHOT FOR THE LADIES.
KIM RIGHT DOWN THROUGH AN OPEN
TARGET.
LEIF CONNECTS BUT NOT ENOUGH.
CHELSEA UP FOR THE LADIES.
CHELSEA JUST MISSES.
JONAS CONNECTS BUT NOT QUITE
ENOUGH.
NEXT TWO.
ALL RIGHT, MONICA.
MONICA'S BACK WAY DEEP.
MONICA RELEASES AND OBLITERATES
A TARGET FOR THE WOMEN!
COLTON GOES HIGH.
NOTHING BUT AIR FOR THE MEN.
NEXT TWO.
TARZAN TAKES AIM.
TARZAN HITS THE FRAME.
SABRINA LETS IT RIP AND
OBLITERATES ANOTHER TARGET FOR
THE WOMEN.
THE WOMEN HAVE CONNECTED TWO IN
TWO DIFFERENT PLACES,
HORIZONTALLY AND VERTICALLY.
NEXT TWO.
YOU'RE LOOKING TO CONNECT FIVE.
COME ON, CHRISTINA.
CHRISTINA READY.
DAMN!
Jeff: JAY REARS BACK.
JAY CONNECTS FOR THE MEN.
THE MEN NOW HAVE TWO CONNECTED
IN THAT CENTER ROW.
NEXT TWO.
ALICIA'S BACK.
AND THAT'LL DO IT.
THE WOMEN NOW HAVE THREE
CONNECTED STRAIGHT DOWN THE
MIDDLE.
MICHAEL WAY SHORT.
DIDN'T EVEN GET TO THE TARGET.
LEIF GOES HIGH BUT TOO HIGH.
KIM FIRES AND CONNECTS KNOCKING
OUT THE FOURTH TARGET FOR THE
WOMEN!
AH, CRAP.
Jeff: WOMEN NOW IN THE LEAD
WITH ONLY ONE TARGET LEFT, THE
BIG CHOICE OF REWARD.
OKAY, IT'S ON.
JASON, BABY, YOU'RE THE MAN.
YOU'RE GONNA DO IT, NEW.
RIGHT.
Jeff: JONAS IS UP FOR THE
MEN.
COME ON, JASON!
Jeff: .
HIS NAME IS JONAS.
Jeff: JONAS GOES WAY BACK
ON THAT PLATFORM AND HE CONNECTS
FOR THE MEN!
WAY TO GO, JONAS!
Jeff: CHELSEA KNOCKS OUT
ANOTHER TARGET GIVING THE WOMEN
MORE OPTIONS.
THE MEN HAVE THREE CONNECTED IN
THE CENTER ROW.
THE WOMEN HAS ONE TARGET IN
MIND.
BOTTOM ROW, CENTER TARGET FOR
THE WIN.
COLTON NOT WASTING ANY TIME.
HE'S BACK AND READY.
TOO HIGH!
COLTON RIGHT THROUGH AN EMPTY
TARGET.
MONICA CAN WIN IT RIGHT HERE
MONICA DOES IT FOR THE WOMEN!
WOMEN WIN THEIR THIRD STRAIGHT
CHALLENGE!
AND A CHOICE OF REWARD!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
WHOOP, WHOOP, WHOOP.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WOMEN.
THREE CHALLENGES IN A ROW.
(SCREAMING)
GUYS HAS MOMENTUM FINALLY
SHIFTED.
IS THIS WHAT IT TAKES, THREE IN
A ROW?
NO, LUCK!
Jeff: LUCK?
PURE LUCK.
LUCK, I DON'T THINK SO.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WOMEN.
THREE VERY DIFFERENT CHOICES OF
REWARD.
OH, MY GOD.
A DIET, GIRLS, GOT TO BE
TARP.
YEAH, TARP.
IT'S GOT TO BE TARP.
Jeff: WHAT'S THE CHOICE?
CHOICE IS THE TARP, JEFF.
Jeff: WOMEN, GET YOUR
REWARD, HEAD BACK TO CAMP AND
GET IT SET UP.
NICE JOB.
GREAT JOB, LADIES.
BYE!
OH, YEAH, BYE, BYE.
Jeff: WELL, WHAT APPEARED
EARLY ON TO HAVE THE MAKINGS OF
A BLOWOUT IS CLEARLY A VERY
COMPETITIVE GAME BETWEEN THE MEN
AND THE WOMEN.
GUYS, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ANOTHER "W" BABIES.
GOOD JOB, EVERYONE.
GOOD JOB.
THEY THOUGHT THEY HAD IN THE
THE BAG.
SALANI ON THREE?
ONE, TWO, THREE, SALANI!
IT WAS SO GOOD TO WIN THE
REWARD CHALLENGE.
WHEN WE HIT THAT LAST ONE YOU
COULD TELL IT SUCKED ALL THE AIR
OUT OF THEM.
I DIDN'T CARE.
TARZAN WAS OVER WITH HIS CRUSTY
ASS TALKING ABOUT "IT'S JUST
LUCK, IT'S JUST LUCK" LUCK
THESE.
SO WHAT THEY GOT A TARP.
THE CHALLENGE ITSELF WAS KIND
OF A FLUKE.
WE DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO
LEARN THE GAME.
NEITHER DID THEY, THOUGH.
IT'S PRETTY MUCH DEAD EVEN.
THEY HAVE A TARP; WE HAVE A
TARP.
THE GAME IS NOT EASY, DUDE,
WE'RE UP ONE PERSON.
I WILL TAKE ONE PERSON UP OVER
ALL THE DOUGHNUTS IN THE WORLD.
TO BE HONEST, WE GOT OUR
BUTTS KICKED.
THESE WOMEN AREN'T SLOUCHES SO
WE NEED TO STOP THINKING ABOUT
THEM AS JUST SOME CHICKS OVER
THERE BECAUSE THE MOMENTUM AND
"OH, WE'VE WON THREE; THEY'VE
WON THREE" THAT'S OUT THE
WINDOW, MAN!
WE JUST NEED TO WIN THESE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES, BRO.
I KNOW.
THOSE CHICKS ARE TOUGH.
THOSE ARE SOME SERIOUS
COMPETITORS, MAN.
FOR SURE, DEFINITELY.
I'D LOVE TO FIND AN IDOL.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
THAT'D MAKE ME FEEL SO MUCH
BETTER.
I'M DEFINITELY GLAD TO
ACTUALLY BE ABLE TO TALK TO YOU.
WHEN COLTON SAID TO VOTE FOR
YOU, I DIDN'T REALLY WANT THAT,
YOU KNOW?
COLTON SAID THAT?
YEAH.
WOW.
AND... DON'T TELL HIM THAT.
I WON'T.
AND THEN EVERYONE CAME TO THE
DECISION THAT IT SHOULD BE MATT
BECAUSE, I MEAN, WE DIDN'T
REALLY KNOW WHERE YOUR HEAD WAS
AT AND, I MEAN, WE'RE ALL ON THE
SAME PAGE NOW.
BOYS AND GIRLS, BILL JUST GOT
WOWED.
TURNS OUT MY NAME WAS WAY MORE
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK THAN I
THOUGHT IT WAS AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENS
BRO.
THAT'S THE NAME OF THE GAME.
NAME OF THE BEAST.
THIS CHANGES EVERYTHING, NOW
THAT I KNOW THE GLOVES ARE OFF
AND IT'S ANYBODY'S GAME.
JUST KEEP EVERYTHING BETWEEN
US, YOU KNOW?
IF I FIND AN IDOL, BRO, I'LL
LET YOU KNOW, I SWEAR IT.
I SAW LEIF TALKING TO BILL
AND, LIKE, THEY WERE A GOOD
CONVERSATION.
I SWEAR TO GOD IT'S THAT GUY
LEIF, MAN.
THAT LITTLE MUNCHKIN IS ABOUT
TO GET KNOCKED BACK TO OZ.
WHERE IS HE?
CALL LEIF OVER HERE.
HEY, LEIF.
COLTON WANTS YOU.
THE MISFITS ARE RUNNING THE SHOW
RIGHT NOW.
I THINK THERE'S A TARGET ON MY
BACK SO I NEED TO DO SOMETHING
AND COLTON AND I WERE TALKING
ABOUT LEIF BECAUSE I SEE LEIF AS
WORKING ALL SIDES HERE.
SO I BROUGHT LEIF INTO THE MIX
JUST TO ADD ONE MORE CUSHION IN
FRONT OF ME.
DID YOU TELL BILL THAT HE WAS
NEXT?
DID I TELL BILL?
YEAH.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO... I
DIDN'T TELL HIM.
I DIDN'T STRAIGHT UP TELL HIM,
YEAH, WE'RE VOTING FOR YOU, BRO.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
I'M GIVING YOU A CHANCE RIGHT
NOW.
IF YOU TOLD HIM, TELL ME, AND
I'LL TRY TO DO WHAT I CAN.
BUT IF YOU LIE TO ME AGAIN...
WHAT DID YOU TELL HIM?
I DIDN'T EVEN SAY THAT.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
OKAY, YES, I DID.
YOU TOLD HIM?
I APOLOGIZED.
YOU TOLD HIM WE WERE AFTER
HIM?
YOU PRETTY MUCH SEALED YOUR
FATE.
IT'S A TIGHT RACE BETWEEN LEIF
AND BILL FOR WHO IS THE MOST
WISHY-WASHY PLAYER IN THIS GAME.
BILL'S MORE SNEAKY WHEREAS LEIF
IS MORE STUPID.
HE'S TURNING INTO AN ANNOYING
LITTLE OOMPA LOOMPA.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT NO ONE
HERE TRUSTS YOU?
I KNOW.
YOU ARE DIGGING YOUR OWN
GRAVE.
I KNOW.
I JUST...
WELL, I TOLD YOU TO PICK A
SIDE AND YOU PICKED THE WRONG
SIDE.
TODAY I PUT THE BIGGEST
ULTIMATE FOOT IN MY MOUTH AND
RIGHT NOW EVERYBODY HAS REALLY
LOST TRUST IN ME.
I REALLY HOPE THAT I CAN SOMEHOW
REGAIN THAT BECAUSE IF NOT I
COULD POSSIBLY BE GOING HOME.
I REALLY DID IT THIS TIME.
TREEMAIL!
LOOKS LIKE A PUZZLE.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS LET'S ALL PUT
IT TOGETHER.
CORNERS.
ANOTHER CORNER.
ALL RIGHT.
"WHEN PAIRS OF MINDS WORK
TOGETHER, BEING WELL BALANCED IS
AN IMPORTANT PART.
YOU CAN'T OUTRUN A VOTE AGAINST
YOU, SO TODAY YOU'LL JUST HAVE
TO BE SMART.
WHEN PAIRS OF MINDS WORK
TOGETHER" SO WE'RE WORKING IN
TWOS.
I WOULD LIKE TO BE PARTNERED
WITH SOMEONE WHO'S GOOD AT
PUZZLES BECAUSE I'M BAD AT THEM.
WE CAN USE THE SAME PARTNERS.
YOU'RE GOOD AT PUZZLES?
I JUST PUT THAT TOGETHER,
REALLY.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT THAT.
ARE YOU CALL MEGASTUPID?
IT SEEMS LIKE WE HAVE TO DO A
PUZZLE AND RIGHT AWAY KAT SAYS
"I DON'T WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
YOU CAN'T DO NO PUZZLES."
AND RIGHT THEN AND THERE THAT
PISSED ME OFF AND I HAD TO CHECK
HER.
ME INTENTION WASN'T SAYING
THE PARTNER I HAD LAST TIME
WASN'T SMART ENOUGH TO BE MY
PARTNER NOW.
THAT'S HOW YOU TOOK IT?
I SO DIDN'T TAKE IT THAT WAY.
I TOOK IT THAT WAY.
OKAY, WE'RE NOT GOING TO
RECAP IT.
KAT WAS SAYING LOOK, I'M NOT
THE BRIGHTEST STAR IN THE
UNIVERSE WHEN IT COMES TO
PUZZLES AND ALICIA TOOK IT VERY
PERSONAL CAUSING CONTROVERSY
MINUTES BEFORE OUR CHALLENGE
WHERE WE NEED TO HAVE OUR MINDS
STRAIGHT.
YOU ALREADY KNOW WE'RE A HOT
MESS IN HERE WHEN IT COMES TO
COMMUNICATION BUT ALICIA STUCK A
FIRECRACKER, THAT'S STUFF WE
DON'T NEED RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES!
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
WILL TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
BE PAIRED UP AND TIED TOGETHER.
ON MY GO, EACH PAIR WILL RACE
ACROSS TEETER-TOTTERS TO GET TO
A PUZZLE.
SOLVE THE PUZZLE, BRING BACK A
KEY, THE NEXT PAIR GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE SOLVED THE REMAINING
PUZZLES AND COLLECTED ALL THREE
KEYS, ONE PERSON WILL USE THOSE
KEYS TO OPEN THREE LOCKS.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO OPEN THEIR
THREE LOCKS AND RAISE THEIR
TRIBE FLAG WINS IMMUNITY, AVOIDS
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
MEN, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON.
BILL SAT OUT THE LAST CHALLENGE,
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE THIS TIME?
ME.
Jeff: JONAS, TAKE A SPOT ON
THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WORK ON
YOUR PAIRS THEN WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
LET'S GO, GUYS.
Jeff: CHELSEA AND ALICIA
THE FIRST COUPLE FOR THE WOMEN.
TARZAN AND COLTON THE FIRST
COUPLE FOR THE MEN.
GOT TO GET OVER THE
TEETER-TOTTER AND SOLVE THAT
PUZZLE.
GO, GO!
Jeff: THE WOMEN ARE FIRST
TO THE PUZZLE.
THEY'RE PUTTING LOGS TOGETHER
AND THEY WILL LINE UP.
THAT GOES HERE.
COLTON AND TARZAN MAKING
PROGRESS.
THIS GOES HERE.
THERE WE GO.
Jeff: GUYS HAVE IT.
HEAD BACK.
WE HAVE TO KEEP GET THE KEY!
OH, GET THE KEY!
Jeff: LADIES STARTING TO
FALL BEHIND BUT IT'S A LONG
CHALLENGE.
NEXT TWO GO.
GOD!
Jeff: JAY AND MICHAEL
HEADING OUT FOR THE MEN.
RIGHT AFTER THAT, SECOND PUZZLE.
GO, GO!
Jeff: JAY AND MICHAEL.
FOUR PIECES NEED TO FORM A
PYRAMID.
THREE CORNER BASE!
THIS IS NOT WORKING.
RIGHT HERE.
WHAT'S GOING ON OVER THERE?
Jeff: THE WOMEN ARE STILL
WORKING ON THAT FIRST PUZZLE.
IT IS THE EASIEST PUZZLE AND
IT'S TAKING THEM A LONG TIME.
.
COME ON, FELLAS, YOU GUYS GOT
THIS.
COME ON, GUYS!
YES!
Jeff: GUYS HAVE THEIR
SECOND PUZZLE.
THEY HAVE PUT THE PYRAMID
TOGETHER QUICKLY.
JAY AND MICHAEL HEADING BACK.
THE WOMEN STILL WORKING ON THEIR
FIRST.
TROYZAN AND BILL HEADING OUT
NOW.
GOING TO WORK ON THE THIRD AND
FINAL PUZZLE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE WE CAN'T GET
THIS.
CHELSEA, JUST LOOK AT THEIR
PUZZLE.
NO, NO, DO NOT DO THAT.
IT'S THE LONG PIECE...
OH, LOOK AT THAT!
IS.
Jeff: CHELSEA STARTING TO
LOOK NEXT DOOR TO SEE IF SHE CAN
FIGURE OUT HOW THE GUYS DID IT.
CHEAT!
KISS MY ASS.
CHEATER, CHEAT!
Jeff: TROYZAN AND BILL
START WORK ON THE SLIDE PUTZLE
WITH A GIGANTIC LEAD.
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
GOOD WORK, BABY.
Jeff: THIS IS HARD TO
BELIEVE!
THE WOMEN HAVE CHECKED THE MEN'S
PUZZLE, THEY'VE GONE OVER AND
LOOKED AT IT AND STILL CAN'T GET
IT TOGETHER.
YOU GUYS SUCK, YOU KNOW THAT?
THAT'S IT!
Jeff: THE WOMEN HAVE IT
FINALLY, TAKE OFF THAT FIRST KEY
AND GET A MOVE-ON.
THE MEN HAVE HAD A LOT OF TIME
TO WORK ON THIS SLIDE PUZZLE AND
THEY'RE MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS.
KIM AND SABRINA HEADING OUT TO
THAT SECOND PUZZLE.
THE ONLY GOOD NEWS TO BEING
BEHIND IS THERE'S A MODEL RIGHT
NEXT DOOR TO LOOK AT.
HEY, QUIT LOOKING AT OUR
PUZZLE!
CHEATER!
DON'T YOU DO THAT.
TARZAN, YOU'RE GOING TO GET
SLAPPED, DUDE.
YEAH!
COME ON, BOYS!
Jeff: THE MEN HAVE THEIR
THIRD PUZZLE SOLVED.
THEY'VE GOT THE THIRD KEY AND
THEY'RE HEADING BACK.
COME ON, TROY!
COME ON, BILL!
YAY!
Jeff: THE MEN HAVE THREE
KEYS.
ALL THEY HAVE TO DO IS OPEN
THREE LOCKS AND IMMUNITY IS
THEIRS ONCE AGAIN.
Jeff: .
DON'T GIVE UP GIRLS, WE GOT
IT.
(LAUGHS)
Jeff: LEIF HAS THE FIRST
LOCK UNDONE.
YES!
Jeff: LEIF HAS THE SECOND
LOCK OPEN.
IT'S NOT ONE WORLD, IT'S
LEIF'S WORLD.
Jeff: LEIF HAS THE THIRD
LOCK UNDONE!
LEIF RAISES THE FLAG!
MEN WOMEN IMMUNITY!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
MEN, CONGRATULATIONS.
(APPLAUSE)
IMMUNITY ONCE AGAIN IS YOURS.
(CHANTING)
THAT WAS A BLOWOUT.
THAT BARELY QUALIFIED AS A
CHALLENGE.
ALICIA, YOU AND CHELSEA WERE
STILL WORKING ON THE FIRST
PUZZLE AND THE MEN WERE NEARLY
DONE WITH THE ENTIRE CHALLENGE.
I KNOW.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
Jeff: HOW DO YOU LAUGH?
IT'S LIKE, "OH, CAN'T WAIT TO
TELL EVERYBODY HOW BAD THAT
WAS."
NOT AT ALL.
I THINK I LET THEM DOWN.
THAT WAS AN EASY PUZZLE AND I
DON'T KNOW WHAT WENT WRONG.
Jeff: YOU WALKED OVER,
LOOKED AT IT AND COULDN'T GET
IT.
I HEAR YOU.
Jeff: MEN, NO TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT, ENJOY THE NIGHT
OFF.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
NICE WORK.
WOMEN, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY ELSE FROM YOUR TRIBE
WILL BE OUT OF THIS GAME FOR
GOOD.
YOU HAVE TO AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT WILL BE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALICIA'S ATTITUDE AFTER THE
CHALLENGE WAS REPULSIVE.
BUT THAT ACTUALLY CAN BE TO MY
ADVANTAGE BECAUSE NOW ALL THE
GIRLS ARE COMING TO THINK THAT
IT'S TIME FOR ALICIA TO GO AND
WHEN THERE'S A WEAK LINK, YOU'VE
JUST GOT TO TAKE IT OUT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
GREAT JOB.
SWEET.
EVERY SINGLE PERSON PULLED THEIR
WEIGHT.
THAT'S IT FOR THOSE GIRLS,
MAN.
HE'S BACK IN OUR CAMP.
THAT ONE WE CAME THROUGH AND
WE CRUSHED IT.
WE PULLED OUT A WIN WHEN WE
DEFINITELY NEEDED IT, MAN.
AND IT MAY HAVE SAVED MY BUTT
BECAUSE I'M ON THE OUTS WITH THE
TRIBE BUT NOW WE'RE NOT GOING TO
TRIBAL AND IT'S NICE TO SEE THAT
LITTLE RED DEVIL BACK AT CAMP.
OKAY, I KIND OF WANT TO KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
I.
I'M NOT MAKING ANY EXCUSES
BUT IT DID LOOK A LOT EASIER
THAN IT WAS.
CHELSEA AND I WE REALLY DID
TRY AND I THINK FOR THE MOST
PART WE DO A GREAT JOB IN OUR
OTHER CHALLENGES SO HOPEFULLY
THAT DOESN'T...
THAT COULD HAVE BEEN ANY ONE
OF US.
TOMORROW IS A NEW DAY.
WHEN IT COMES TO CHALLENGES,
I'M USED TO PEOPLE JUST LIKE,
YOU KNOW, LET'S GO TO WAR.
SO ALICIA LAUGHING ABOUT THE
LOSS, THAT RIGHT THERE PISSED ME
OFF.
THAT'S LIKE SALT IN THE WOUND
TODAY.
ALICIA IS JUST DEAD WEIGHT WITH
A MOUTH.
LET ME KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
ALICIA'S GOT TO GO.
WHAT?
ALICIA DOES NOT WANT TO BE
HERE.
SHE HAS NO FIGHT.
I KNOW BUT... I JUST DON'T
KNOW THAT CHRISTINA'S
CONTRIBUTING ANY MORE THAN
ALICIA.
SHE'S CONTRIBUTING A LOT MORE
AT CAMP.
NO DOUBT.
AND WHO'S HAD BEEF BETWEEN
PEOPLE?
THAT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
FOR SURE I THOUGHT CHRISTINA
WAS THE LOCKED IN VOTE TO GO.
SO THE MOOD IS WEIRD NOW.
SABRINA IS TRYING TO SHAKE
THINGS UP AND THAT MAKES ME A
LITTLE NERVOUS.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GOING TO BE AN INTERESTING
AFTERNOON.
HEY COLTON.
WHAT?
LET ME TALK TO YOU FOR A
MOMENT.
WHY?
I WANT TO SQUASH SOME BEEF,
HANDLE IT LIKE ADULTS.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, WE'RE NOT VOTING ANYONE
OFF.
YO, YO, LISTEN, PERSON TO
PERSON, HUMAN TO HUMAN, MAN TO
MAN.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR THAT
CRAP.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR THAT CRAP.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU RIGHT
NOW.
LISTEN, BRO, I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU DON'T LIKE ME, MAN, OR WHAT
I'VE DONE TO UPSET YOU.
ALL I KNOW IS YOU HAVE BEEN
THE MOST WISHY-WASHY PLAYER IN
THIS ENTIRE TRIBE.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO.
OH, MY GOD, BILL YOU'RE GOING
HOME NEXT, THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
THE FOUR OF US WENT OVER...
BYE.
THERE'S CLEARLY FRICTION
BETWEEN ME AND COLTON SO I WENT
TO HAVE A CHAT WITH HIM MAN TO
MAN AND HE DECIDED HE DIDN'T
WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
AND NOTHING GETS ME MORE
FRUSTRATED THAN WHEN SOMEBODY
DOES NOT WANT TO TALK.
WHEN I DON'T LIKE SOMEONE I
DON'T WANT TO SEE THEM, I DON'T
WANT TO TALK TO THEM, LIKE I
DON'T WANT TO BE AROUND THEM.
I DON'T WANT TO BE AROUND YOU.
PERIOD.
SO DON'T FOLLOW ME.
LISTEN..
OH, MY GOD, I SWEAR.
LISTEN YOU LITTLE STUCK UP
BRAT, I'M TELLING YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I'M GOING TO VOTE YOUR ASS
OUT.
YOU DON'T SIT AROUND AND TALK
TO PEOPLE EVERYTHING YOU WANT
TO.
NO, NO.
MOVE.
NO, DUDE.
I ABSOLUTELY HATE BILL.
I HATE HIS VOICE.
I HATE HIS JOKES.
HE'S NOT FUNNY.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, I'M A STANDUP
COMEDIAN.
SHUT UP.
GET A REAL JOB.
YOU ARE DISGUSTING.
I HATE HIM.
I WANT HIS HEAD ON A PLATTER.
I WANT HIM GONE.
BILL JUST ATTACKED ME LIKE GOT
UP IN MY FACE.
LIKE STARTED YELLING AT ME.
LEIF TOLD HIM THAT HE WAS NEXT.
THAT'S WHAT LEIF SAID?
WHAT A BUNCH OF KNUCKLE
HEADS.
BILL IS A CRAZY PERSON.
I HATE HIM MAYBE I SHOULD GO TO
THOSE GIRLS AND SAY DO Y'ALL
WANT TO TRADE AND WE'LL GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE WE HAVE
MORE TO DEAL WITH.
THAT WOULD BE INTERESTING.
WOULD YOU BE WILLING?
BECAUSE HERE'S THE THING... I
KNOW Y'ALL WANT TO GO TO THE
MERGE WITH NUMBERS BUT IF YOU GO
TO THE MERGE WITH NUMBERS THAT
AREN'T ON YOUR SIDE IT DOESN'T
MATTER.
THAT'S A... I'VE NEVER HEARD
OF ANYONE DOING THIS.
WE JUST WON IMMUNITY AND
COLTON'S SAYING WE SHOULD GIVE
IT AWAY.
AND I'M THINKING WHAT?
THIS IS A HUGE MOVE, DUDE.
BUT IT'S A SMART MOVE IN THE
END.
I DON'T LIKE THAT IDEA BUT AT
THIS POINT COLTON'S CALLING THE
SHOTS.
SO WHAT AM I GOING TO SAY, NO?
IF I DO THAT, COLTON MIGHT PUT A
TARGET ON MY BACK.
WE CAN GIVE THE GIRLS
IMMUNITY AND GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL AND VOTE OUT BILL.
SAY WHAT?
YEAH.
SHUT UP!
HONESTLY.
THIS IS GOING TO BE THE SMARTEST
MOVE FOR US BECAUSE...
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I THINK THAT'S A HASTY DECISION.
LEIF TOLD BILL HE WAS GETTING
VOTED OUT.
BILL GOES CRAZY.
SO NOW COLTON'S LIKE LET'S GIVE
THE GIRLS OUR IMMUNITY IDOL AND
VOTE BILL OUT RIGHT NOW.
BUT LEIF IS A LOOSE CANNON, TOO.
HE'S WORKING BOTH SIDES.
LET'S THINK ABOUT IT FOR A
SECOND.
YEAH.
LISTEN, BUDDY...
I AGREE.
LET'S GIVE...
WE'VE GOT TO GO IN NOW AND DO
THAT.
WHEN A GROUP OF MEN GET
TOGETHER AND MAKE A PACT, YOU
BETRAY THEM, THAT'S A BREACH OF
FAITH.
SO WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT
THIS AND WE'VE GOT TO DO IT
TONIGHT.
WE'RE THINKING OF LETTING YOU
GUYS STAY AND WE GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WHY?
WE HAVE A BETRAYAL.
WHAT HAPPENED?
THEY WANT TO GO TO TRIBAL.
ARE YOU JOKING?
NOPE.
OH, MY GOD!
THEY'VE REALLY LOST THEIR
MIND.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, LEIF, I'M
SORRY, BUT WHAT YOU DID IS
EGREGIOUS.
YOU SHOULD NOT HAVE DONE THAT.
THAT WAS BAD.
AND THE BEST THING TO DO IS GIVE
THE GIRLS THE IDOL AND GO TO
TRIBAL TONIGHT RATHER THAN
SMOLDER ABOUT IT FOR GOD KNOWS
HOW MANY DAYS.
WAIT.
WHEN WE GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN?
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE LEIF OUT.
TARZAN GAVE THIS HUGE SPEECH
ABOUT HOW HE'S SENDING LEIF HOME
BUT I THOUGHT COLTON WANTED TO
VOTE OUT BILL.
SO I'M LIKE WHAT IN THE WORLD IS
GOING ON?
WHAT DO YOU THINK ALL OF US
SHOULD DO?
I TRULY AM SORRY, GUYS.
I MEAN I JUST WANT TO BE 100%
YOU WITH YOU GUYS.
YOU HAVE BETRAYED US.
THAT MEANS YOU WILL NOT BE
TRUSTED AND YOU WILL BE, WHETHER
YOU VOTE ON THIS TONIGHT OR NOT,
BULL THE FIRST TO GO.
IT'S AMAZING.
I MEAN, THEY'VE GOT DRAMA IN
THEIR HOUSE AFTER A WIN.
I DON'T CARE.
LET THEM FALL APART.
I WOULD LOVE NOT TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THE MANONO TRIBE HAS
ABSOLUTELY LOST THEIR MARBLES.
THEY'RE NOT A TRIBE.
THEY'RE NOT WORKING TOGETHER.
WHICH IS GREAT BECAUSE IF THEY
DO THIS, IT GIVES THE SALANI
TRIBE THAT BIG BOOST THAT WE
NEEDED.
OKAY, MIGHT AS WELL VOTE.
WE ALL HAVE TO AGREE ON IT
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T DO IT UNLESS
WE ALL AGREE.
WHO WANTS TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL RAISE THEIR HAND.
I DO.
COME ON.
HOW ABOUT YOU, BILL?
MAN THIS GAME IS CRAZY.
BUT IF I VOTE WITH THE REST OF
THE GROUP TO GO TO TRIBAL AND
VOTE LEIF OFF WELL HE'S IN HOT
WATER AND PEOPLE ARE ANGRY, THAT
SERVES MY PURPOSE IMMENSELY.
I'LL HAVE YOU GUYS KNOW I AM
COMPLETELY BUM-PUZZLED RIGHT
NOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF
THIS.
THE GUYS ARE VERY CONFUSED
RIGHT NOW.
BUT I'VE ALWAYS BEEN ABLE TO GET
PEOPLE TO DO WHAT I WANT AND I
WANT BILL GONE.
I'M RUNNING THIS ENTIRE SHOW
RIGHT NOW.
IF YOU CAN'T SEE THAT, YOU ARE
HELEN KELLER.
JUST KNOW THIS, NO
FOOLISHNESS LIKE THAT WOULD EVER
GO DOWN IN THIS TRIBE.
EVER.
NO WAY.
I JUST HOPE WE DON'T HAVE TO
GO TO TRIBAL AND VOTE SOMEBODY
OFF.
24 SEASONS, SOME 400 TRIBAL
COUNCILS.
NEVER HAD A TRIBE ARRIVE AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL AFTER WINNING
IMMUNITY.
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY, TROYZAN?
YOU'RE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL!
THE ONE PLACE YOU DO NOT WANT TO
BE IN THIS GAME.
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED WAS
EVERYONE GOT TOGETHER AND AGREED
TO GIVE THE IMMUNITY TO THE
GIRLS BECAUSE AS A TEAM WE
WANTED TO VOTE BILL OUT.
BUT LEIF BASICALLY SAID BILL
WE'RE VOTING YOU OUT SO HE KIND
OF BROKE THE TRUST OF EVERYBODY.
IT WAS LIKE YOU JUST COMMITTED,
LIKE, THE CARDINAL SIN TO US AND
SO AS A GROUP WE SAID THAT CAN'T
HAPPEN.
YOU HAVE TO GO.
Jeff: SO LEIF WAS A MEMBER
OF YOUR ALLIANCE.
YES.
Jeff: HE WAS IN ON IT AND
WENT AND BLURTED IT.
YES.
Jeff: SO LEIF YOU BLURT
THIS OUT AND THEN ALL HELL RAINS
DOWN ON YOU.
YEAH, I'M DEFINITELY A GUY
THAT JUST TRIES TO PLAY WITH MY
HEART ON MY SLEEVE AND IT BIT ME
IN THE BUTT.
Jeff: PLAYING WITH YOUR
HEART ON YOUR SLEEVE DOESN'T
MEAN GIVING UP INFORMATION FROM
AN ALLIANCE.
WELL, I KNOW BILL AND I HAVE
DEFINITELY BEEN GETTING CLOSER
ON LIKE A MORE FRIEND LEVEL AND
THAT'S WHAT IT WAS.
I MEAN, HE ASKED AND I TOLD HIM.
Jeff: AND YOU UNDERSTAND
STRATEGICALLY HOW DANGEROUS THAT
IS.
YEAH.
I MEAN RIGHT NOW I'M PRETTY MUCH
GOING HOME.
BUT BY PUTTING MYSELF UP FOR
ELIMINATION I REALLY HOPE THAT
IT PROVES TO THE GUYS THAT I
STILL HAVE INTEGRITY WITHIN OUR
GROUP.
Jeff: JAY, WHY IS IT SO
URGENT TO GIVE UP IMMUNITY?
WHY NOT JUST SAY "ALL RIGHT,
NEXT TIME WE HAVE TO VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT, LEIF, IT'S YOU"?
YOU KNOW, WHEN I FIRST HEARD
OF THIS IT WENT OVER MY HEAD
LIKE ARE YOU GUYS KIDDING?
WE DEMOLISHED OUR ENEMY AND YOU
WANT TO HAND OVER THE IDOL.
Jeff: BUT YOU SAID YES.
I DID.
IF I DON'T GO WITH THE MAJORITY
I COULD BE THE NEXT ONE TO GO.
I'M NOT TRYING TO PUT A TARGET
ON MY BACK SO RELUCTANTLY, YES,
I SAID YES.
Jeff: BILL, WHAT ARE THE
CHANCES THAT THIS WILL GO DOWN
AS THE SINGLE DUMBEST MOVE EVER
IN THIS GAME?
DUMBER THAN SOMEBODY GIVING UP
THEIR INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
THIS IS A TRIBE!
EIGHT PEOPLE AGREED TO DO THIS!
I MEAN, THIS COULD BE THE
SINGLE DUMBEST MOVE.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T KNOW UNTIL IT
PLAYS OUT BUT THERE'S NO POINT
IN GOING INTO A MERGE IF YOU
HAVE SOMEBODY WHO CAN'T BE
TRUSTED.
Jeff: COLTON, WHERE DID
THIS IDEA FIRST START?
WHEN DID YOU HEAR ABOUT IT?
WHEN WE REALIZED THAT LEIF
HAD TOLD BILL, LIKE, I'M THE
TYPE OF PERSON IN THIS GAME THAT
IF I DON'T LIKE YOU I'M NOT
GONNA TALK TO YOU.
LIKE, I WILL JUST IGNORE YOU,
LIKE LEAVE ME ALONE.
Jeff: WHO DON'T YOU LIKE IN
THIS GAME?
BILL.
(LAUGHS).
Jeff: WHY DON'T YOU LIKE
BILL?
HE'S OBNOXIOUS, HE'S LOUD.
AND, PLUS, HE'S A "STRUGGLING
STANDUP COMIC."
I DON'T GET WHAT YOUR
CORRELATION IS.
LIKE, GET A REAL JOB!
Jeff: WOW, BILL.
HONESTLY, I LOVE THE KID TO
DEATH.
WE JUST COME FROM TWO TOTALLY
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS.
BUT THE THING ABOUT IT IS...
WAIT, YOU JUST SPOKE.
GIVE ME A SECOND.
ME AND HIM COME FROM TWO
ENTIRELY DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS.
I'M NOT HERE TRYING TO MAKE IT
THIS WHOLE BLACK WHITE THING OR
WHATEVER.
I'M JUST TALKING ABOUT THE
DIFFERENCES IN OUR UPBRINGINGS,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I'VE BEEN ON MY OWN SINCE I WAS
17 YEARS OLD, MAN.
ME BEING POOR, THAT'S JUST MY
LIFE.
WHEN YOU'RE A STRUGGLING STAND
UP COMIC, THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
YOU DON'T MAKE VERY MUCH MONEY,
YOU SLEEP ON PEOPLE'S COUCHES
AND YOU GO FROM GIG TO GIG.
THE TRUTH IS, THAT'S WHAT I DO.
Jeff: SO COLTON, TELL ME
ABOUT WHERE YOU COME FROM.
ALABAMA.
I MEAN, I LIVE A TOWN OF 3,000
PEOPLE.
AND, YES, I DID GO TO A PRIVATE,
LIKE, ALL-WHITE SCHOOL.
BUT I DO HAVE, LIKE, AFRICAN
AMERICAN PEOPLE IN MY LIFE.
Jeff: WHO?
(LAUGHS)
MY HOUSEKEEPER!
SO, I MEAN, LIKE, THAT JUST
PUT US ON A WEIRD VIBE FROM DAY
ONE.
BUT SHE'S, LIKE, A MEMBER OF
OUR FAMILY.
Jeff: A PAID MEMBER.
YES.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW... SHE DOESN'T
WORK FOR FREE.
BUT I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM WITH
BILL BECAUSE OF HIS RACE AT ALL.
THE PROBLEM I HAVE WITH BILL IS
THAT HE'S POOR PITIFUL ME I'M
POOR.
LIKE, I DON'T ASSOCIATE WITH
PEOPLE LIKE THAT IN THE REAL
WORLD AND I'M SURE AS HELL NOT
GOING TO ASSOCIATE WITH PEOPLE
LIKE THAT OUT HERE.
Jeff: SO BEING A STANDUP IS
NOT A LEGITIMATE PROFESSION IN
YOUR EYES?
NO, IT IS A LEGITIMATE
PROFESSION BUT HAVING A BACKUP
PLAN.
LIKE, DON'T LIVE OFF THE
KINDNESS OF OTHERS.
Jeff: .
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
BRO, YOU HAVEN'T WORKED AN
HONEST DAY IN YOUR LIFE OR HAD
TO ACTUALLY GO OUT AND GET A
JOB.
YOU'RE GOING TO SIT UP HERE AND
TELL ME THAT ME PURSUING MY
DREAM, SOMETHING THAT I LOVE,
WHICH IS COMEDY, I DON'T WANT A
FALLBACK PLAN.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO DO WITH MY
LIFE.
OKAY...
HOLD ON.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO DO WITH MY
LIFE.
DON'T JUDGE ME.
I DON'T JUDGE YOU.
SO DON'T LOOK DOWN AT ME.
DON'T CALL ME NAMES.
AND FOR THE LOVE OF GOD I WORK
WITH PEOPLE AND FOR NO ONE.
YOU GOT THAT?
WHATEVER, BILL.
Jeff: KOHL ON THE, ARE
THERE ANY GROUPS WHERE YOU LIVE
THAT LOOK DOWN OR MAYBE JUDGE
THE FACT THAT YOU'RE GAY?
I'M SURE THERE ARE.
BUT THE PEOPLE THAT I ASSOCIATE
WITH, YEAH, Y'ALL CAN SAY
COUNTRY CLUB PEOPLE, WHATEVER, I
FEEL LIKE THEY HAVE MORE
EDUCATED THOUGHTS AND IDEAS AND
THEY'RE MORE OPEN AND ACCEPTING
TO THINGS.
THE ONES WHO HAVE A PROBLEM WITH
IT ARE THE ONES RIDING AROUND IN
THEIR, LIKE, JACKED UP CHUCKS
WITH THE REBEL FLAGS HANGING IN
THE BACK AND THEY GO HOME TO
THEIR TRAILERS AT NIGHT.
Jeff: TARZAN?
ALL I WANT TO SAY IS THIS
CONVERSATION HAS DEVOLVEED INTO
A NUMBER OF SOCIAL PLATITUDES
UNFAIR TO BOTH GUYS AND AS FAR
AS I CAN TELL COLTON'S BEEN
PAINTED IN THE WRONG LIGHT,
WHICH IS EASY ENOUGH TO DO.
Jeff: WHAT LIGHT IS THAT?
WELL, HE'S BEEN PAINTED AS A
RICH KID THAT NEVER HAD TO LIFT
A FINGER AND...
Jeff: PAINTED BY WHO?
OKAY, HERE'S THE DEAL.
THE WHOLE THING ABOUT RACE IRKS
ME.
I THINK IT'S TIME TO QUIT
TALKING ABOUT (BLEEP)ING RACES.
I'M FED UP WITH PEOPLE TALKING
ABOUT RACE!
I'M TIRED OF IT!
I WANT PEOPLE TO BASE WHAT THEY
THINK ABOUT SOMEBODY ON HOW THEY
BEHAVE AND WHAT THEIR MERITS ARE
AND NOTHING ELSE.
I DON'T CARE WHAT COLOR THEY
ARE.
THAT'S HOW PEOPLE SHOULD DO.
AND I THINK THIS COUNTRY IS
MOVING IN THAT DIRECTION.
WE HAVE A BLACK PRESIDENT!
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
Jeff: IT'S VERY INTERESTING
WHAT'S DEVELOPED HERE TONIGHT.
THE DIFFERENCES THAT YOU GUYS
BRING INTO THIS GAME ARE A VERY
BIG PART OF WHAT WILL EITHER GET
YOU TO THE END OR END UP GETTING
YOU VOTED OUT AS IS GOING TO BE
THE CASE TONIGHT.
YOU TWO MAY NEVER HAVE MET IN
NORMAL LIFE.
NEVER.
BUT YOU'RE HERE TODAY AND THE
ONLY WAY TO GET TO THE END IS
EITHER WITH EACH OTHER OR
THROUGH THE OTHER.
AND REGARDLESS HOW THIS VOTE
COMES OUT, THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL
WILL GO DOWN AS ONE OF THE
CRAZIEST IN THE HISTORY OF THIS
GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JAY, YOU'RE UP.
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
I'M NEVER GONNA LIKE YOU SO
PLEASE TAKE YOUR BROKE ASS HOME.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION THE FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LEIF.
BILL.
TWO VOTES BILL; ONE VOTE LEIF.
THREE VOTES BILL; ONE VOTE LEIF.
BILL.
FOUR VOTES BILL, ONE VOTE LEIF.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: ONE WORLD," BILL,
THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
BILL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, VOLUNTARILY GIVING UP
IMMUNITY WILL GO DOWN AS ONE OF
THE BIGGEST AND RISKIEST MOVES
EVER SEEN IN THIS GAME.
TIME WILL TELL IF THIS ONE PAYS
OFF.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, LET'S HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
ALL HAIL TO THE QUEEN!
Jeff: COLTON'S REIGN
CONTINUES.
BLAH WHAT'S THE PLAN?
I COULD BE COLTON'S BITCH, I'LL
BE WHATEVER YOU WANT ME TO BE.
Jeff: BUT A TWIST KNOCKS
HIM OFF HIS THRONE.
BEFORE WE GET TO THE
CHALLENGE...
OH, MY GOD!
I JUST THOUGHT BEEP!
MY TRIBE IS DOING SOME VERY
UNORTHODOX THINGS.
BUT SINCE I WAS PROBABLY NEXT ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK ANYWAY, I
CAME TO TRIBAL COUNCIL TO ROLL
THE DICE.
ONE DAY COLTON WILL BE PUT IN A
SITUATION WHERE HE CAN'T JUST
NOT LIKE SOMEBODY BECAUSE
THEY'RE NOT PEOPLE THAT HE'S
USED TO OR THAT HE'S GROWN UP
WITH.
HE JUDGED ME BECAUSE OF MY
DIFFERENCES AND I ACCEPT HIM