Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": WHEN THE TWO TRIBES
MERGED INTO ONE, KIM WAS PLAYING
BOTH SIDES.
WE HAVE TO TELL EACH OTHER
WHAT'S ANYTHING DOWN AND MAKE
SURE IT GOES.
I HAVE AN ALL-WOMEN'S
ALLIANCE, AND I HAVE MY SALANI
ALLIANCE.
Jeff: WHEN THE TIME CAME,
KIM OPTED TO GO WITH THE WOMEN
AND TAKE OUT THE MEN.
THIS IS NEVER GOING TO BE THE
SAME.
IT'S TIME FOR THE GUYS TO KNOW
WHERE THE WOMEN STAND.
Jeff: TROYZAN AND JAY, THE
TWO STRONGEST REMAINING MEN,
BECAME UNEASY.
I JUST DON'T WANT THEM TO TRY
TO FULL SOME PAST MOVE ON US.
Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, CHELSEA CAME OUT ON
TOP.
CHELSEA WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
WITHOUT THE PROTECTION OF AN
IMMUNITY NECKLACE, TROYZAN
DECIDED IT WAS TIME TO MAKE A
DESPERATE MOVE.
YEAH, BABY.
I HAVE AN IDOL, BRO.
I'M PLAYING IT.
IF I GET TARZAN TO VOTE FOR KIM,
AND I GET CHRISTINA TO VOTE FOR
KIM, WOULD YOU VOTE FOR KIM.
Jeff: DESPITE HIS EARLIER
SUSPICIONS, JAY MAINTAINED HIS
ALLIANCE WITH THE WOMEN.
HE'S DEBATING ON PLAYING THE
IDOL.
I FIGURED.
TROY IS JUST CONCERNED THE
WOMEN HAVE THE NUMBERS.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO
BLINDSIDE HIM, BUT I TRUST MY
TWO GIRLS.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
JEFF...
Jeff: TROYZAN MADE GOOD ON
HIS IDOL THREAT.
I'M NOT GOING TO JOIN THAT
GROUP.
Jeff: ANY VOTES CAST
AGAINST TROYZAN WILL NOT COUNT.
WITH THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IN
PLAY, THE WOMEN'S SPLIT VOTE,
MEANT JAY WAS SENT PACKING.
THE NINTH MEMBER VOTED OFF AND
THE THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JAY.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
LEFT COMPLETELY ALONE, CAN
TROYZAN FIND A WAY BACK IN?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES AND HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
NINE ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
TROY, I KNEW YOU HAD THAT
IDOL.
SAY WHAT?
GOOD HUNCH.
TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS THE
BIGGEST DISAPPOINTMENT SO FAR.
JAY GOT VOTED OUT, SO I'M
BASICALLY NEXT IN LINE,
PROBABLY.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
NOTHING PERSONAL.
TAKE IT AS A COMPLIMENT?
YOU NEVER WERE GOING TO VOTE
ANY OTHER WAY.
CORRECT?
I WAS GOING TO GO WITH
WHATEVER WAS THE INITIAL PLAN.
YOU'VE BEEN ON THE BLOCK TO
GET VOTED OUT, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE LIKE, ALL KYLEED IN.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DID
THAT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SHE'S NOT ONLY ONE HODID
THAT.
THAT'S WHAT'S SHOCKING, TOO.
DON'T ATTACK HER.
I'M NOT ATTACKING HER-- HEY,
I'M ASKING HER A QUESTION.
YOU'RE PUTTING WORDS IN MY
MOUTH.
I CAN ASK HER A QUESTION.
DUDE, RELAX.
I'M NOT RELAXED.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE RELAXED.
I CAN ASK THE QUESTIONS.
DON'T GET CRAZY WITH ME.
I WILL GET CRAZY WITH YOU.
TROY IS DIGGING HIMSELF IN A
BIGGER HOLE.
HE'S ATTACKING EVERYBODY ELSE
AND TRYING TO COP AN ATTITUDE
WITH ME.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE HE SHOULD BE
UPSET WITH ME.
I DIDN'T VOTE FOR HIM.
I'M GLAD YOU ANSWERED FOR
YOURSELF.
AT LEAST SHE DIDN'T ANSWER FOR
YOU.
I'M TOTALLY PISSED OFF.
I FEEL LIKE I'M COMPLETELY ALONE
NOW.
WHEN I GET PISSED OFF, I GET
FIRED UP.
NOW I'M GOING TO WIN EVERY DAMN
IMMUNITY.
I COULD GIVE A CRAP ABOUT THOSE
PEOPLE.
THIS IS NO TEAM ANYMORE.
I'M NO TEAM PLAYER.
THIS IS JUST TROYZAN VERSUS
EVERYBODY ELSE.
THAT'S THE WAY I FEEL.
LISTEN,UN, IT'S REALLY NOT
FAIR THAT THREE OR FOUR PEOPLE
THAT DID TO ME.
I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD BE HERE
BEFORE THEY SHOULD GO.
I JUST FEEL LIKE WHAT THE HELL
ARE THEY DOING?
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE DOING HERE.
I'M JUST-- IT'S JUST THE
GAME.
THIS IS HOW RIDICULOUS THESE
PEOPLE ARE.
THEY SOMEHOW THINK I'M SUPPOSED
TO COME BACK TO CAMP, "IT'S JUST
A GAME.
HEY, WE'RE JUST HAVING FUN
HERE."
I'M LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU KIDDING
ME RIGHT NOW?
I HAVE THE RIGHT TO BE ANGRY.
AS MUCH AS I HATE TO SAY IT,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE IT LIKE JONAS.
HE TOOK IT LIKE A MAN AND HE
DESERVES TO BE HERE MORE THAN
MAYBE YOU.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
HE WORKED HIS ASS OFF HERE
EVERY SINGLE DAY AND HE TOOK IT
LIKE A MAN.
RIGHT.
THESE GIRLS ARE KIND OF ACTING
LIKE WHAT A LOT OF WOMEN ACT
LIKE IN REAL LIFE-- THEY GET
THEIR HOUSE.
THEY GET THEIR FOOD.
THEY GET ALL THEIR SUCH.
THEN AS SOON AS THEY FEEL
SATISFIED, THEY GO, GUESS WHAT?
WE DON'T NEED YOU NO MORE.
YOU'RE DONE.
WE'RE DONE WITH THE GUY.
TREE MAIL WITH A BUNCH OF
ENVELOPES FOR EACH OF US.
WOW.
WOW!
WITH OUR NAMES ON IT!
HOW BEAUTIFUL!
YOU READY FOR THIS?
"GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
THIS SHOULD BE SOME FUN.
SPEND YOUR CASH IN CLEVER WAYS
AND YOUR HUNGER WILL BE DONE."
CAN I PUT A 20 DOWN FOR A
TURKEY OR SOMETHING.
THIS IS CASH MONEY WE GO TO
TREE MAIL AND IT'S AN AUCTION.
THEY'RE ALL TALKING ABOUT, OH,
IT'S FOOD.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT FOOD.
IF GET TO THE AUCTION AND JEFF
SAYS, LISTEN, HERE'S A NOTE THAT
CAN HELP YOU FURTHER IN THE
GAME, I'M BUYING THAT THING.
I'M SPENDING 500 BUCKS.
THAT'S ALL I'VE GOT.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WELCOME TO THE "SURVIVOR"
AUCTION.
YOU EACH HAVE 500 U.S. DOLLARS.
BIDDING IS IN INCREMENTS OF 20
DOLLARS.
YOU CANNOT POOL YOUR MONEY.
YOU CANNOT SHARE YOUR ITEM.
SHALL WE GET STARTED?
YES.
Jeff: FIRST ITEM.
I SMELL PEANUT BUTTER.
Jeff: YOU SMELL WRONG.
I WANT PEANUT BUTTER.
Jeff: THREE DONUTS AND AN
ICED COFFEE.
ICED COFFEE?
KIM.
I'M GOOD.
Jeff: KIM RIGHT OUT OF THE
GATE, 100 BUCKS.
120.
140, 160.
Jeff: 160 TO CHELSEA.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
SOLD, COME ON UP.
GO AHEAD, GIRL.
Jeff: $160 FOR THREE DONUTS
AND AN ICED COFFEE.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: GO AHEAD AND TAKE A
LITTLE SAMPLE.
DELISH.
THANK YOU, SIR.
OH, MY GOD!
THAT LOOKS GREAT!
Jeff: NEXT ITEM.
CHIPS, GUACAMOLE, MARGARITA WITH
ICE.
100.
Jeff: 100 TO ALECIA?
ONE EIGHT TOW 220.
320?
FOUR.
Jeff: 400 DOLLAR BID FROM
SABRINA.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: GOING ONCE, TWICE,
SOLD. OH, GOD.
IT SMELLS SO GOOD.
STRAIGHT FROM MEXICO.
OH!
I WANT TO BUY SOMETHING.
Jeff: NEXT ITEM, THIS IS A
PROTEIN BOOST.
THIS IS FOR SOMEBODY WHO IS
LOOKING FOR A LITTLE ENERGY,
PROTEIN SHAKE WITH BANANAS MIXED
IN AND A COUPLE ON THE SIDE.
60.
Jeff: FOURTH TO KAT.
60 TO LEIF.
100.
Jeff: 100 TO LEIF.
$100 GOING ONCE, TWICE, SOLD TO
LEIF.
COME ON UP.
GOOD JOB, LEIF.
Jeff: TAKE A SIP.
THANK YOU, SIR.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
GET YOUR BUTT BACK OVER HERE.
MMM-MMM.
Jeff: NEXT ITEM, "SURVIVOR"
SHOWER WITH WITH SHAMPOO AND
TOOTH BRUB.
20 BUCKES.
Jeff: 20 TO ALICIA?
20--
OH.
YOU DO 40.
IT GOES IN 20s.
I'LL DO 40.
Jeff: 40 TO KIM.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
I WANT FOOD.
Jeff: KIM JUST BOUGHT A
SHOWER FOR $40.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I JUST GAVE
THAT TO HER FOR 40 BUCKS.
Jeff: HAVE FUN.
THANKS.
THIS IS HILARIOUS.
TARZAN, DON'T STARE.
WHOOO!
OH, MY GOD!
FOR 40 BUCKS?
Jeff: NEXT ITEM B.L.T.,
CHIPS, AND A COLD ICED TEA.
40.
100.
Jeff: 100 TO KAT.
ONE 60.
180.
Jeff: 180 TO KAT.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
SOLD TO KAT, $180.
OH, THERE'S BACON ON THERE!
DID YOU JUST SAY THERE'S
BACON.
AND HE CLEARLY SAID THAT WAS A
B.L.T.?
I KNOW.
Jeff: NEXT ITEM, I
ANTICIPATE A BIDDING WAR.
20 BUCKS 20 BUCKS.
200.
Jeff: FROM THE SHOWER, KIM
BIDS 200.
THAT WAS THE ONE
THINGIMENTED.
Jeff: GOING ONCE, GOING
TWICE--
WAIT, WAIT A SECOND.
Jeff: 200.
220.
Jeff: 220 TO ALAES 2 FOURT
TO THE WOMAN IN THE TOWEL.
DON'TING CHEAP!
Jeff: GOING ONCE, GOING
TWICE, SOLD TO KIM.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: CRAZEST AUCTION EVER,
HALF-NAKED WOMAN IN A TOWEL NOW
HAS CHOCOLATE AND PEANUT BUTTER.
I'M NOT GOING TO PAY 200.
Jeff: ALICIA, YOU WERE GIVEN
$500.
I KNOW, I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO
GET WORKED UP.
DON'T HATE ME BECAUSE I'M
EATING THIS PEANUT BUT NERT
SHOWER.
Jeff: TARZAN, YOU HAVEN'T
THOUGHT ABOUT BIDDING.
I HAVE SHOCKS FOR MY JEEP
THAT I HAVE TO REPAIR.
THIS WILL DO IT.
Jeff: ARE YOU PUTTING ME
ON?
NO, HE'S DEAD SERIOUS.
I WAITED THREE MONTHS TO FIX
MY SHOCKS, AND THIS DOES IT?
Jeff: NEXT ITEM.
BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE YOU HEARD
FROM YOUR LOVED ONE.
LETTERS FROM HOME.
OH, NO!
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: ALL OF YOUR LETTERS.
OPENING BID.
$500.
Jeff: THIS ITEM IS SOLD.
$500 TO ALAES.
ALL OF YOUR MONEY.
WHO'S IT FROM?
SOMEONE EVEN WROTE ME?
MY DAD HAS NEVER WROTE ME
ANYTHING IN MY LIFE.
ALICIA, I HOPE ARE YOU DOING
WELL.
I THINK ABOUT YOU, YOUR SOLITUDE
ALL THE TIME.
I READ SOMEWHERE THAT
PREPARATION POWERS PERFORMANCE.
KNOW THAT YOU ARE PREPARED.
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE BETTER
PREPARED SO JUST GIVE IT YOUR
BEST.
SEE YOU SOON.
POLICE OFFICER, DAD.
OH!
Jeff: WORTH THE MONEY?
EVERY PENNY.
OKAY, TARZAN.
IT'S OKAY.
Jeff: WELL, HERE'S THE
DEAL.
THE PRICE HAS BEEN SET, A STEEP
ONE AT THAT, $500.
BUT THAT IS THE PRICE OF A
LETTER.
ANYBODY ELSE HAS $500.
I'LL GIVE YOU 500.
Jeff: YOU CAN BUY IT RIGHT
NOW.
OH!
Jeff: TARZAN GOING TO SPEND
THAT.
THE CAR REPAIR WILL HAVE TO
WAIT.
COME ON UP, TARZAN.
ENJOY.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: TARZAN, DO YOU WANT
TO SHARE?
NO.
Jeff: DOES IT PUT THE CAR
REPAIR IN PERSPECTIVE?
I THINK YOU MADE THE RIGHT
CHOICE.
YEAH.
Jeff: TROYZAN, WHAT ARE YOU
MISSING RIGHT NOW?
I FEEL COMPLETELY ALONE.
AFTER LAST NIGHT.
Jeff: AFTER THE LAST
TRIBAL?
YEAH.
I JUST FEEL I'M ALONE.
AND TO KNOW THAT I HAVE A LETTER
THERE, MAYBE FROM MY BROTHER OR
MY DAD.
ENCOURAGING ME.
IT'S GOOD, BUT IT'S JUST THE
FEELING OF, LIKE, I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING ON MY OWN.
Jeff: LAST SHOT AT LOVE
LETTERS.
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MONEY.
I DON'T, EITHER.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NEXT ITEM.
AN ADVANTAGE IN THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
WOW.
300.
Jeff: 300 TO TROYZAN.
GOING ONCE.
I DON'T HAVE THE MONEY.
I DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH MONEY.
CHRISTINA, YOU HAVEN'T SPENT
A DIME.
Jeff: 360 TO CHRISTINA AT
THE LAST SECOND.
THREE 80.
GET IT, CHRISTINA.
400.
420.
CALL FIVE.
Jeff: 420 TO TROYZAN.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
SOLD TO TROYZAN FOR $420.
DAMN RIGHT.
WE'RE STILL GOING TO VOTE YOU
OFF.
Jeff: WHY THE BIG FIST
SLAM?
BECAUSE IT PISS ME OFF.
Jeff: WHAT ANNOYS YOU?
THAT THEY WANT ME OUT OF
HERE.
SO THEY'RE BASICALLY-- IT'S A
TEAM AGAINST TROY.
THAT'S WHY I SAID I FEEL ALONE,
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL SITTING
THERE, "GO UP MORE, GO UP MORE."
AND POOR CHRISTINA IS LIKE, THE
FREAKING GUINEA PIG.
YOU DON'T THINK CHRISTINA
WANTED IT ALL?
BUT SHE WANTED IT FOR THE
TEAM.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALL IN FAVOR OF
CHRISTINA GETTING IT.
YOU DIDN'T SAY LIKE, WOW, GREAT
JOB, TROY, YOU GOT THAT THING.
GREAT JOB, TROY, YOU GOT IT.
WELL, AFTER THE FACT.
Jeff: TOUGH GAME, HUH,
SABRINA?
IT IS.
BUT IT'S THE NATURE OF THE GAME.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WINNER.
I STILL HAVE MONEY LEFT.
LET'S GO.
Jeff: NEXT ITEM.
YES, I'M HUNGRY.
Jeff: WILL REMAIN COVERED
AND IT COMES WITH A NOTE.
60.
Jeff: 60.
80.
Jeff: 80.
100.
Jeff: 100 BACK TO KAT.
120.
160.
Jeff: 160 TO KAT.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE--
LET IT ROLL.
Jeff: SOLD TO KAT.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS WHAT YOU
BOUGHT FOR $160.
OH, MY GOD!
GET OUT OF HERE!
Jeff: HERE'S THE NOTE THAT
COMES WITH IT.
READ THE NOTE OUT LOUD.
YOU JUST BOUGHT THIS CAKE FOR
THE ENTIRE TRIBE.
( CHEERS )
YOU HAVE 60 SECONDS TO EAT IT.
I CALL THE STRAWBERRIES.
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT HERE, RIGHT
HERE.
Jeff: 60 SECONDS START NOW.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: "SURVIVOR" AUCTION IS
OFFICIALLY OVER.
SO, YOU KNOW, LEAVING THE
AUCTION, I GOT A NOTE, AN
ADVANTAGE TO THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, ANY CHALLENGE, IF YOU
CAN GET AN ADVANTAGE, HEY, TAKE
IT.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU WILL MOVE DIRECTLY TO THE
SECOND STAGE OF THIS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
YOUR ODDS OF WINNING IMMUNITY
HAVE JUST INCREASED FROM ONE IN
NINE TO ONE IN FOUR, BABY."
THAT'S RIGHT, BABY.
I'M WINNING THIS THING.
I HAVE TO WIN.
HE'S KNUCKLEHEADS DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY GOT THEMSELVES INTO.
YOU CANNOT MESS WITH TROYZAN.
YOU THINK YOU HAVE ME
OUTSMARTED.
THEY DON'T.
THEY'RE VERY SCARED, AND THAT
TELLS ME SOMETHING.
I'M THINK, HECK.
THAT IMMUNITY IDOL, IF THERE'S A
NEW ONE OUT THERE, I'M GOING TO
START LOOKING.
I'LL DO IT IN FRONT OF
EVERYBODY.
I DON'T REALLY CARE.
YOU PUT FEAR IN PEOPLE'S HEARTS
AND YOU CAN SCRAMBLE THEM A
LITTLE BIT.
OH, I HATE THIS!
HOW DOES HE EVEN KNOW THERE
IS AN IDOL.
WE DON'T, BUT THERE ARE EIGHT
OF US AND ONE OF HIM AND IF WE
ALL GO LOOKING FOR IT THE
CHANCES OF US FINDING IT ARE FAR
GREATER THAN HIM FINDING IT.
WHEN JEFF BROUGHT OUT THE
LETTER THAT WOULD GIVE SOMEONE
AN ADVANTAGE ON THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, WE KNEW
CHRISTINE AFTERSHOCK THE ONLY
ONE THAT STILL HAD ENOUGH MONEY
LEFT THAT COULD TAKE IT FROM
TROY.
AND WHEN SHE BACKED OUT, I THINK
EVERYONE JUST WAS LIKE OH!
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
SO ANNOYING.
THE WAY I SEE IT IS THAT TROY
HAS PUT THE CROSSHAIRS ON HIS
BACK.
IT'S EIGHT AGAINST ONE RIGHT
NOW.
WE JUST WANT TO TAKE HIM DOWN
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
BUT RIGHT NOW, TROY IS GOING TO
PUT MORE HEART INTO THIS GAME
THAN MOST OF THE PEOPLE HERE.
I SEE KIM, LIKE, LOOKING AT
ME, AND I PULL OUT THE LITTLE
PIECE OF CLOTH, AND I START
STUFFING IT IN AND ACT LIKE I'M
ZIPPING SOMETHING UP.
LETTING THEM THINK I HAVE AN
IDOL.
I NEED TO KNOW WHAT THAT FOOL
FOUND.
I'M ACTING MORE COCKY NOW,
BECAUSE I BASICALLY CAN.
I'VE GOT NOTHING TO LOSE.
THEY'RE ALREADY LOOKING AT ME
LIKE WHAT'S IN HIS POCKETS, YOU
KNOW?
I WANT THEM THINKING I'VE GOT
IT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUST SAY
HYPOTHETICALLY HE DID FIND IT.
IF HE FOUND AN IDOL, WE'LL FLUSH
IT OUT WITH THE VOTES.
EVENTUALLY HE'LL BE GONE.
IT SUCTION HE HAS THE
ADVANTAGE IN THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
IT'S ABOUT AS BIG A DISASTER AS
COULD HAVE HAPPENED AT THE
AUCTION TODAY.
IF HE FOUND IT AND HE WON THE
IMMUNITY IDOL, THAT WOULD BE A
TWO BUMMER.
THAT WOULD BE THE ABSOLUTE
WORST IF HE WINS IMMUNITY AND
HAS THE IMMUNITY IDOL ON TOP OF
THAT.
IT'S DISASTER.
HE'S GOING TO BE LIKE, YOU KNOW,
SCARY.
WHO KNOWS WHAT HE CAN PULL OFF.
HE'S A REALLY SMART GUY.
SO HOPEFULLY WE CAN GET RID OF
HIM BEFORE HE DOES SOMETHING TOO
CRAZY THAT SENDS ME HOME.
LOOK, EVERYBODY GETS CRAZY
WHEN THEY KNOW THE WHOLE TRIBE'S
AFTER YOU.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THAT ONE
PERSON NEVER WINS.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
YES.
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
CHELSEA, I'M COMING FOR IT.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
RACE TO UNTANGLE KNOTTED ROPES.
THE FIRST FOUR TO FINISH WILL
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND WHERE
YOU WILL RACE UP A STACK OF
CRAITS, BOUNCE A COCONUT OFF A
TRAMPOLINE, ATTEMPTING TO KNOCK
OUT YOUR TARGETS.
THE FIRST TWO MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND WHERE YOU WILL USE A
SLINGSHOT TO FIRE COCONUTS AT A
WALL OF TARGET.
FIRST PERSON TO KNOCK OUT THREE
TARGETS IN A ROW, EITHER
HORIZONTAL, VERTICAL, OR
DIAGONALLY, WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND
GUARANTEED A ONE IN EIGHT SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
AFTER 27 DAYS, SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT.
TROYZAN, AT THE AUCTION, YOU
SPENT NEARLY ALL OF YOUR MONEY
TO BUY ONE THING, AN ADVANTAGE
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
OPEN THE NOTE.
READ IT.
OKAY.
"ACCUSATIONS.
YOU WILL MOVE DIRECTLY TO THE
SECOND STAGE OF THIS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE."
ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: TROYZAN SITS OUT THE
FIRST ROUND.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, WE WILL CRAW FOR
SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST THREE TO FINISH MOVE ON TO
THE NEXT ROUND WHERE YOU WILL
JOIN TROYZAN.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
GOT TO UNTIE THE BUNDLE OF ROPES
TO THE RING AT THE END.
TROYZAN SPENT OVER $400 TO SKIP
THIS STEP.
WHILE EVERYBODY ELSE WAS EATING,
HE WAS WORRIED ABOUT THIS
CHALLENGE.
SABRINA PICKING UP THE PACE.
KAT DOING A NICE JOB.
A LOT OF PEOPLE IN THIS.
VERY CLOSE.
THREE PEOPLE MOVING ON.
TARZAN VERY CLOSE.
KIM VERY CLOSE.
CHRISTINA'S IN THIS.
TARZAN ON HIS LAST BITS OF ROPE.
KIM ON HER LAST BITS.
CHRISTINA ON HER LAST BITS.
CHELSEA TRYING TO CATCH UP.
THREE PEOPLE ARE MOVING ON.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE RING, STEP ON
YOUR MAT.
TARZAN, THE FIRST TO MOVE ON!
CHRISTINA VERY CLOSE.
KIM HAS HER RING.
SHE'S MOVING ON.
CHRISTINA HAS A RING.
SHE'S MOVING ON!
CHRISTINA, KIM, AND TARZAN WILL
JOIN TROYZAN IN THE SECOND
ROUND.
YA!
Jeff: HERE WE GO.
FIRST TWO TO FINISH MOVE ON TO
THE FINAL ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
Jeff: THIS IS A RACE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT YOU CAN GO.
COME ON!
Jeff: TARZAN KNOCKS OUT HIS
FIRST TARGET.
NICE, KIM.
Jeff: KIM JUST MISSES.
Jeff: TROYZAN CONNECTS.
TROYZAN HAS ONE TARGET OUT.
TARZAN JUST MISSED.
KIM MISSES AGAIN.
Jeff: CHRISTINA.
TROYZAN HITS HIS SECOND TARGET.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
.Jeff: KIM HITS HER FIRST
TARGET.
TROYZAN HAS ONE TARGET LEFT.
JUST MISS.
KIM KNOCKS OUT HER SECOND
TARGET.
TARZAN HITS HIS SECOND TARGET.
CHRISTINA STILL EMPTY-HANDED.
Jeff: TROYZAN KNOCKS OUT
HIS THIRD TARGET.
COME ON!
Jeff: HE'S MOVING ON TO THE
FINAL.
THIS IS MY ISLAND.
YOU CAN'T BEAT ME.
SHUT UP.
OH, PLEASE.
OH, OH, MY GOD.
PLEASEIOC THIS FOOL OUT.
Jeff: WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE
MORE PERSON IN THE FINAL TO JOIN
TROYZAN.
Jeff: TARZAN TAKING AIM.
THIS COULD DO IT.
AND IT DOES!
TARZAN MOVES ON TO THE FINAL
JOINING TROYZAN.
ALL RIGHT, BABE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT, BABE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT, GIRL.
Jeff: HERE WE GO.
FINAL ROUND, TARZAN VERSUS
TROYZAN.
GRAB A COCONUT.
GO UP TO THE SLINGSHOT.
IT'S ONE SHOT AT A TIME.
YOUR GOAL-- KNOCK OUT THREE IN A
ROW, EITHER HORIZONTAL,
VERTICALLY, OR DIAGONALLY.
FIRST TO DO IT WINS IMMUNITY.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST SHOT.
THREE, TWO, ONE, LAUNCH.
TROYZAN CONNECTS AND TARZAN
CONNECTS.
NICE, BABY!
Jeff: BOTH CONNECT ON THEIR
FIRST HIT.
GREAT JOB.
YOU GOT THIS, TARZAN.
Jeff: NEXT ROUND, THREE,
TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
Jeff: TROYZAN CONNECTS ON
HIS SECOND SHOT.
IT'S OKAY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: TARZAN JUST MISSES.
TROYZAN IN THE LEAD NOW.
KNOCKING OUT TARGETS IS PART OF
THE GOAL.
MAKING THEM IN A LINE IS THE
KEY.
NEXT SHOT WHEN YOU'RE READY.
TROYZAN KNOCKS OUTAISE THIRD
TARGET.
TARZAN KNOCKS OUT HIS SECOND
NICE, BABY.
Jeff: BOTH GUYS ONE SHOT
AWAY FROM WINNING.
TROYZAN TRYING TO HIT EITHER THE
LOWER LEFT TARGET OR DEAD CENTER
IN THE MIDDLE TO CONNECT THREE.
TARZAN NEEDS TO HIT THE LOWER
LEFT.
HERE WE GO.
TROYZAN MUST WIN THIS CHALLENGE
TO STAY IN THIS GAME.
AND JUST MISSES.
TARZAN KNOCKS OUT HIS THIRD
TARGET.
NIERKS BABY.
TARZAN NOW HAS A FEW MORE
OPTIONS FOR THE WIN.
HE CAN GO TOP LEFT, BOTTOM LEFT,
OR MIDDLE BOTTOM.
COULD BE THE LAST SHOT RIGHT
HERE.
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
TARZAN JUST MISSES.
TROYZAN KNOCKS OUT HIS THIRD
TARGET IN A ROW.
YES!
Jeff: TROYZAN WINS
IMMUNITY.
YES!
DON'T ( BLEEP ) WITH ME.
THAT'S, LIKE--
YOU JUST BOUGHT ONE ROUND.
THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING TO CONTINUE LIKE
THAT.
I'M COMPETITIVE.
LET'S GO, THEN, KEEP BRINGING
IT.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, KEEP BRINGING IT.
LET'S GO.
YOU GUYS ARE SCARED TO DEATH.
OH, REALLY?
WHAT?
I'VE BEEN GOING 50%.
NOW, LET'S GO.
YOU WANT TO KEEP SCRAMBLING, DO
IT.
Jeff: TROYZAN, COME ON
OVER.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU DEFINITELY
NEEDED IT.
YOU EARNED IT.
TROYZAN IS SAFE AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
CONGRATS.
THANK YOU.
CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
YES, YOU MAY.
OF COURSE.
YOU NEED TO KNOW, I LIKE YOU.
BUT, PLEASE, IF YOU WIN, BE
NOBLE.
IT LOOKS BAD.
I'M HIGHLY COMPETITIVE
PERSON.
THIS IS THE WAY THAT I AM.
EVERYONE'S PERSONALITY IS
DIFFERENT.
I'M FRUSTRATED BECAUSE I KNOW
EVERYONE'S AGAINST ME.
IF THERE WERE SEVEN PEOPLE
AGAINST YOU AND YOU JUST FELT
LIKE YOU BEAT SEVEN PEOPLE, YOU
MIGHT SCREAM, TOO.
I CAN'T CHANGE MY PERSONALITY
MIDSTREAM AND BE LIKE, OH, I
WANT TO BE SOME NOBLE GUY AND
JUST GO LIKE-- BOW.
I JUST WANT TO SAY.
I'M YOUR FRIEND.
SHAKE MY HAND.
I'M STILL ANYTHING TO TRY TO
BEAT YOU.
OKAY, GREAT.
I WOULD HOPE THAT YOU WOULD.
OKAY.
THIS THING FEELS OUTSTANDING.
IT IS LIKE A-- IT CHANGES MY
WHOLE DAY.
IT CHANGES EVERYBODY ELSE'S
HAPPY-GO-LUCKY MOOD TO, NOW
WHAT?
PARANOIA.
DOES HE HAVE AN IMMUNITY IDOL AS
WELL?
IT'S LIKE THEIR WORST-CASE
SCENARIO, THEIR WORST-CASE
SCENARIO.
TROY WINS.
THOUGHT.
HUH?
THOUGHTS?
WELL, WHAT I THOUGHT IS WE
KEEP OUR STRONGEST WOMEN IN TILL
WE HAVE TO TAKE THEM OUT.
ABSOLUTELY.
THE SECOND THOUGHT IS HE HAS
AN IDOL.
YOU THINK?
I THINK.
THEN MY SECOND THOUGHT WAS, IF
WE TOOK ANOTHER GUY OUT, I'D SAY
LEIF.
BUT THEN IT'S LIKE THAT'S
SOMEONE WE COULD BEAT OVER A
GIRL.
BUT IF WE TAKE A GIRL IT'S JUST
GOING TO--
I THINK-- THAT'S MY THOUGHT.
I THINK AS LONG AS LEIF'S HERE
WE NEED TO KEEP IT SIMPLE.
IF WE TRY TO PULL A MOVE, HE'LL
FEEL IT, HE'LL GET WIND OF IT.
HE'LL FLIP EVERYTHING UPSIDE
DOWN.
THE ONE THING ALL OF US
DIDN'T WANT TO HAPPEN TODAY WAS
FOR TROY TO WIN AND IT HAPPENED.
SO IMMEDIATELY YOU START TO
THINK ABOUT TRIBAL.
I THINK IF WE WERE TO TAKE A
GIRL OUT RIGHT NOW, IT WOULD DO
NOTHING BUT CREATE CHAOS AND
PARANOIA, AND THAT'S THE LAST
THING WE NEED RIGHT NOW.
SO IT'S EASY TO TAKE EITHER
TARZAN OUT OR LEIF OUT.
SO EVERYONE'S VOTING ME OUT?
WHAT.
EVERYONE'S VOTING ME OUT.
YOU OR ME.
ONE OF THE TWO OF US.
YEAH.
MAYBE.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
THEY MAY GO AFTER--
HAVE YOU TALKED TO ANYBODY AT
ALL?
THEY'RE BEING VERY COY.
SO I DON'T CARE.
YEAH.
I SHOULD HAVE WON TODAY.
THEN I'D BE SAFE.
BUT I COULDN'T-- I COULDN'T BEAT
HIM.
HE'S TOO GOOD.
THE BEST STRATEGY FOR ME
TONIGHT IS I'M GOING TO TALK TO
LEIF, CHRISTINA, ALAES, AND
TARZAN.
I'M GOING TO BE POINT BLANK,
LIKE, YOU ARE ON THE BOTTOM.
SO IF YOU'RE STOCK MARKET COME
ALONG WITH ME, AND WE HAVE FIVE
VOTES, AND WE VOTE OUT KIM.
LOOK AT THIS.
HERE'S THE SCENARIO.
IT'S KIM, CHELSEA, KAT, SABRINA.
THOSE ARE FOUR STRONG PLAYERS.
SO NOW I HAVE THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
YOU GUYS HAVE A CHANCE TO DO
SOMETHING HUGE.
I KNOW.
AND IF YOU GET RID OF ONE OF
THOSE PLAYERS, THEN ALL OF A
SUDDEN, YOU CAN PICK THEM ALL
OFF.
WE BREAK OFF THOSE FOUR GIRLS
OVER THERE AND BASICALLY YOU
COULD PICK THEM OFF ONE BY ONE.
IT WOULD NOT BE THAT DIFFICULT.
TO ME THERE ARE FOUR PEOPLE THAT
ARE, LIKE, YOU KNOW, TREATED
LIKE THEY'RE THE BOTTOM.
YEAH.
AND THAT THEY'RE GOING.
YES.
ME INCLUDED.
YOU, LEIF, CHRISTINA AND
ALICIA.
YEAH.
THAT'S FOUR.
I COULD JOIN YOU GUYS TO MAKE
FIVE.
YEAH.
YOU COULD GET RID OF A HUGE
PLAYER.
THAT WOULD BE THE BEST SCENARIO.
THE WORST WOULD BE, LIKE,
PROBABLY IF YOU THEY DECIDE TO
VOTE OUT A LEIF OR CHRISTINA
BECAUSE THAT TAKES AWAY ANY
CHANCE I HAVE OF SITUATION
SOMEONE TO VOTE, AND THE GIRLS
HAVE MAJOR CONTROL.
KIM, CHELSEA, SABRINA AND KAT
ARE TOGETHER.
AND THEY'RE STRONG TOGETHER.
AND THEY'RE NOT GOING TO TELL
YOU GUYS THAT THEY ARE.
THEY'RE JUST GOING TO BASICALLY
ACT LIKE, OKAY, YOU'RE WITH US.
AND THIS IS HOW SHU VOTE.
IF YOU FOUR WOULD GET TOGETHER
AND REALLY GET TOGETHER, YOU CAN
MOVE YOURSELF-- AND I SAID, YOU
KNOW, YOU GUYS CAN MOVE
YOURSELVES AHEAD.
WHY ARE YOU GOING TO STICK WITH
"THE PLAN" IF YOUR PLAN IS
BASICALLY FOR THOSE GIRLS TO
VOTE YOU OUT NUMBER SIX OR
SEVEN, WHATEVER?
YOU KNOW.
FIVE, YOU COULD GO TO FOUR
EASILY.
HELLO!
HI!
WHAT'S TO STOP YOU AND
TARZAN, LEIF, AND CHRISTINA
GETTING RID OF A STRONG PERSON
RIGHT NOW?
NOW IT'S 5-4.
OH, NO, I DEFINITELY
UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
I TOTALLY DO.
AND, LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I DON'T
WANT TO MAKE A RASH DECISION
RIGHT NOW.
OKAY.
BUT, LIKE, THAT IS SOMETHING
THAT I'M NOT CLOSING MY DOOR TO.
OKAY.
>>UN, TROY IS ON TO SOMETHING.
LET'S SAY TROY COMES OUT TO BE
THIS, LIKE, GOD OF, YOU KNOW,
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES.
YOU KNOW, I'M GOING TO SIDE WITH
TROY.
I'M NO DUMMY.
I NEED TO BE THE FIRST ONE.
IT'S SOMETHING I HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT.
I'M HOPING THIS GROUP ALL
COME ALONG WITH ME.
VOTE FOR KIM.
I'LL VOTE FOR KIM AND THEY CAN
ALL BE AT FIVE TODAY.
THIS IS THE ONLY OPPORTUNITY
YOU'RE GOING TO GET.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
BE WITH ME.
YOU CAN'T GO WRONG.
Jeff: I'LL NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JONAS.
MICHAEL.
AND JAY, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO AT BOTH THE AUCTION AND THE
CHALLENGE TODAY, TROYZAN, THERE
WAS A LOT OF ANIMOSITY, A LOT OF
ENERGY DIRECTED REALLY FROM YOU
TO ALL OF THE WOMEN.
CORRECT.
IT'S LIKE I TOLD THEM THAT'S MY
COMPETITIVE JUICES COMING OUT,
AND THAT'S JUST THE WAY I
PLAYED.
IT WAS OBVIOUS THERE WASN'T A
SOUL THAT WAS ROOTING FOR ME.
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT WHEN YOU
POINT IN OUR FACE--
SAY WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT WHEN YOU
POINT IN OUR FACES AND YOU'RE
LIKE, "YOU WILL NEVER BEAT ME.
THIS IS MY ( BLEEP ) ISLAND."
AND YOU SAID ( BLEEP ) YOU.
NO, I SAID DON'T ( BLEEP )
WITH ME.
THERE'S A BIG DIFFERENCE.
DO YOU EXPECT FOR TO US HAVE
A GREAT RECIPROCITY.
NO, WHILE THE THING WAS GOING
ON YOU GUYS COULD GIVE A CRAP.
DON'T MAKE US LOOK LIKE THE
BAD GUYS.
I'M NOT MAKING YOU LOOK LIKE
ANYTHING.
YOU'RE MAKING YOURSELVES LOOK
LIKE WHAT YOU ARE.
YOU'RE A GREAT COMPETITOR,
BUT IN THE LAST 48 HOURS I HAVE
SEEN YOU MORPH INTO A TREATURE I
CAN'T IDENTIFY.
IT'S SO TERRIBLE.
TROYZAN.
THE ULTIMATE TERROR.
BIG DEAL.
DO YOU THINK I REALLY CARE?
I'M SAYING YOU CAN'T BE ALL
EXTREME IN ONE WAY.
NO MATTER HOW LONG YOU OUTWIT,
OUTPLAY, OUTLAST SOMEONE, YOU
HAVE TOOK SOMEWHAT LIKABLE.
YOU'RE NOT MY MOTHER SAYING
WHAT I CAN AND CAN'T DO.
YOU'RE SAYING I CAN TO THIS AND
I CAN'T DO THAT.
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
YOU DID SAY THAT.
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS WRONG.
I'M JUST SPEAKING THE TRUTH.
IF YOU CAN'T HANDLE THE TRUTH--
JEW NOSTHIS IS TRUTH IN
"SURVIVOR."
THERE IS THE ULTIMATE TRUTH
COMING FROM SABRINA WHO
BASICALLY DECEIVED ME AND LIED
TO JAY.
WHAT'S NEXT, MRS. TRUTH?
YOU LIED.
I AM TWO--
DID YOU LIE, YES OR NO?
YES OR NO.
NO.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
WHY ARE YOU GETTING UPSET,
DUDE?
I'M NOT GETTING UPSET.
I'M NOT EITHER.
I'M NOT RAISING MY VOICE.
THIS IS MY TONE OF VOICE.
THIS IS MY TONE OF VOICE AS
WELL.
Jeff: CHELSEA, IN THE
CONTEXT OF COMPETITION, YOU'VE
GOT TO RESPECT A GUY WHO IS
FIGHTING TO STAY IN THIS GAME
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW, IF IT'S MEN
VERSUS WOMEN, YOU HAVE THREE
GUYS WHO ARE IN TROUBLE, UNLESS
SOMETHING HAPPENS.
YEAH, AND TODAY THE WHOLE
PARANOIA THING SET IN.
AND I STARTED THINKING ABOUT THE
OLD MANONO.
Jeff: WHO IS THE OLD
MANONO.
THERE'S TARZAN, LEIF,
CHRISTINA, ALECIA, AND OF COURSE
I THINK TROY IS TRYING TO SWITCH
AND GET ALL THE PEOPLE TOGETHER
ON HIS SIDE.
BUT IT'S, LIKE, TARZAN, LEIF,
AND CHRISTINA ARE GOING NEXT.
IT'S THE FACTS.
KIM, CHELSEA, SABRINA, AND KAT.
THOSE FOUR CAN DO WHATEVER THEY
WANT.
I TOLD THESE GUYS TODAY, LISTEN,
RIGHT NOW, YOU HAVE MY VOTE.
AND YOU HAVE MY FOR IMMUNITIES.
BUT YOU CAN GO FROM GETTING
VOTED OUT TONIGHT, TARZAN,
GETTING VOTED OUT TONIGHT, LEIF,
GETTING VOTED OUT TONIGHT, TO
AUTOMATICALLY GUARANTEE YOURSELF
TO BE AT FIVE, AND THEY CAN DO
IT RIGHT NOW.
IF THEY WOULD VOTE KIM OUT.
THAT'S ALL IT WOULD TAKE.
BUT WHAT YOU'RE PROMISING
THEM IS ONLY GOING TO WORK IF
YOU WIN EVERY SINGLE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
NO, IT'S NOT.
I BEAT YOU ON THE LAST ONE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
ARE YOU BEATABLE.
IF WE'RE A GROUP, YOU DON'T
GET IMMUNITY, WE VOTE SABRINA
OUT.
IF WE'RE SMART WE VOTE KIM OUT
TONIGHT.
IF YOU DON'T GET IMMUNITY, WE
VOTE YOU OUT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE BECAUSE WE
WOULD HAVE FIVE AGAINST FOUR.
YOU CAN'T.
TO ME THE FAULT WITH ALL OF
THIS LOGIC IS EVERYBODY IS
MAKING A LOT OF ASSUMPTIONS, AND
NOBODY KNOWS WHOALIZE WHERE AND
WHO IS WITH WHO.
IF IT WAS THAT SIMPLE AND
CHRISTINA AND ALECIA WERE AT THE
BOTTOM THAT WOULD BE THE TRUTH.
THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
Jeff: KRISTINA, WALK ME
THROUGH WHAT YOU HAVE TO WEIGH
WHEN YOU HEAR TROYZAN'S PITCH.
I MEAN, TROYZAN PUTS OUT A
REALLY INTERESTING PROPOSITION.
IT'S BASIC MATH.
FIVE AGAINST FOUR.
IT ALSO PUTS ME IN AN
INTERESTING SITUATION AS WELL.
LIKE, I DO BELIEVE IN THE
ORIGINAL ALLIANCE I HAD FROM THE
SALANI TRIBE.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS, THIS GAME IS
ABOUT DECEPTION.
THIS GAME IS ABOUT OUTWIT,
OUTLAST, OUTPLAY, SO IT'S GOOD
TO HEAR OPTIONS THAT ARE OUT
THERE.
Jeff: ALICIA, WHAT HAPPENS
IF SOMEBODY FLIPS?
WHAT WOULD DO DO TO THIS GAME?
IF ANY OF US WOULD SPLIT OR
ANY OF US WOULD GO TO TROY, THE
GIRLS WOULD BE SCREWED.
IT'S NOT GOING TO ME.
IT'S FOR YOURSELVES.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
I ALSO HAVE THE SAME CONCERNS AS
CHRISTINA.
DO I TRUST SOMEBODY ALL OF A
SUDDEN NOW?
Jeff: IT REALLY DOES COME
DOWN TO THAT, DOESN'T IT?
WHEN DO I MAKE A MOVE?
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M
STRUGGLING WITH.
Jeff: WELL, ONE THING WE
KNOW FOR SURE, IT WILL NOT BE
TROYZAN.
YOU CANNOT VOTE FOR HIM.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
TROYZAN, YOU'RE UP.
KIM, YOU'RE A FANTASTIC
PLAYER.
AND PROBABLY THE BEST GIRL HERE.
LEIF, I THINK YOU HAVE BEEN
REALLY WISHY-WASHY FROM DAY ONE
AND IT MAKES EVERYONE FEEL A
LITTLE UNEASY.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LEIF.
LEIF.
THAT'S THREE VOTES LEIF.
KIM.
TWO VOTES KIM.
TARZAN.
THAT'S TWO VOTES TARZAN.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES TARZAN.
THREE VOTES LEIF.
TWO VOTES KIM.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, LEIF.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
LEIF, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
BYE, GUYS.
Jeff: WELL, TARZAN AND
TROYZAN, IT WOULD APPEAR YOU
HAVE TWO OPTIONS -- WIN IMMUNITY
OR FIND A WAY IN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR.
THE WOMEN ARE FIGHTING.
THIS IS MY WORST DAY OUT
HERE.
Jeff: TROYZAN MOVES IN FOR
THE KILL.
YOU NEED TO WAKE UP.
WHAT WOULD BE YOUR MASTER
PLAN?
IF YOU WANT ME TO GIVE YOU A
VOTE, I'LL GIVE YOU A VOTE.
I NEED THREE PEOPLE IN WHOM I
CAN BE THE FOURTH AND THAT WOULD
TURN EVERYTHING UPSIDE DOWN.
THAT WOULD BE BEAUTIFUL.
ONE OF THE NUMBER ONE THINGS
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO DO, BEING
ABLE TO SLEEP UNDER THE STARS
AND REALLY JUST TAKE IT ALL IN.
THE WHOLE GUY AND GIRL THING,
THAT DEFINITELY WAS AN
INTERESTING THING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M HERE.
IT KIND OF FEELS LIKE IT WAS
COMING SOONER OR LATER.
I DEFINITELY GAVE IT MY ALL.