Previously on "survivor."
The game began like any other.
It is men versus women.
Men versus women,link
affect on One beach.
even though this is one World,to me
it's their tribe Versus our tribe.
Thend random switch--
we're switching tribes.
changed everything.
four girls in the five-girl
Alliance on the new tribe,price Will.
The new salani stood Strong in
challenges and united As a tribe.
salani!
While the misfits of Mo monano
were at the mercy of Colton.
you can quit or jump in that
Fire,whatever is most Convenient foryo
I*******
When colton was Removed because of a medical
Emergency,the game changed once Again.
Leaving 12 survivors,six
men,And six women,to merge.
there are a couple of ways They think I can find
the Majority,one is with my old Tribe,salani,
the other being a
Potential women's alliance.
While the women were
Keeping their options open.
two days ieg told you that Plan.
don't sprupt me.
The men were at each Other's throats.
you are such a confused,reall
can't Believe you.
I'm done talking with you.
Tarzan also found Himself in hot
water with the Rest of the tribe
It's okay.It's n poop.
It's dirt I stair.
I'm going to puke.Aye be right back.
If it were up to
me,tarzan Would go home.
But at tribal
Council--
seventh person voted Out and the
first member of our Jury. Jonas
It was jonas who was sent home,Leaving
the men at a 6-5 numbers Disadvantage.
Grour torches and head back To camp.
11 are left.Who  be voted out tonight?
***
I***
You know,I befriended
jonas From the beginning,
d I'm Bummed because it's
almost like Luck of the draw.
If jonas would have been on our Team
salani,we would have been Golden.
Mike would have over there and
It wouldn't have been a Question.
you're right.
we got stuck--  playing
with knuckleheads.
we started out men versus Women,but
when they did the old Tribe switch,
me,jay,and mike Made this pact
to stick with the Salani group,
which was chelsea,Kim,kat and sabrina.
I just hope we didn't make a Mistake.
the next decision is easy.
I think it needs to be a girl.
100% it has to be a girl.
I'm really scared at this point
About the girls being together
Because they could very easily
Hook up and they could do Damage.
Honestly,I don't want to be
Overpowered by these girls.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-  Proudly Presents
Sync:Å£±¼ÉÁÉÁºÙ
<font
color=#38B0DE>Survivor.S24E08
****
What***
oh,no.7-up,baby.
Someone's having a party.
you know how good tha
would Taste right now.
The uncola 7-up.
have interesting tree mail.You
have guess what it looks Like.
- oh,my god!
- what!
7-up,the uncoal ababy.
All right,you guys ready?
yes.
your game may be going Downhill quickly.
And must surely have your heart Racing.
When the crisp,clean
taste of Victory today,
and be refreshed From
the stress you're facing.
- riding down something.
- derby race.
that's awesome.
we are definitely drinking Some of this.
I'm gonna love that.
I probably wouldn't even Breathe if I had a
7-up,Would just be down in one gulp.I'm excited.
For me,this is,like,a Necessity.
Come on in,guys!
That's a slide.
that looks like it's
going to Be a big wedgy.
You guys rady to get To
today's reward challenge.
yeah!
For today's challenge You will be
divide dwooided up Into two tribes.
On my go,one at a time you will
Race down a giant waterslide,
And head out into the water Where you will
grab a large Puzzle crate and bring it back.
Then the next person goes.
As more tribenumbers come down The
slide,you'll work together To gather the crates.
Once you have all seven up on Your ptfor you
will use Those craits to solve the Puzzle.
First tribe to get it right wins Reward.
Want to know what you're playing For?
yes!
The winning tribe will
be taken To a 7-up oasis.
oh,my god!
Where you will enjoy An
afternoon barbecue of Burgers.
oh,my god.
Scaek,key lime,Lemon merang pie.
To go along with it,as much
Clean,crisp,refreshing,7-up As you can drink.
- that's awesome.
- oh my god,it's so good.
do we get,like,a little Taste?
I thiou need I Taste.
yeah. yeah.
I think you need ton
What you're playing for?
exactly.
One bottle to share.Who wants it first?
E,me,me.
oh,my god!That was so good!
oh,god.
- Worth playing for?
- yes.
We're going to do a School yard
pick,divide into Tribes.We'll get started.
All right,we have our two Tribes.
Jay,troiz an,kat,alicia,and Chelsea taking
on michael,kim,Sabrina,christina,and lee.
Tarzan,not picked,gonna
sit This one out.
Here we go.
For an afternoon barbecue
at the 7-up oasis.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Jay and mike first down on the Slide.
Nicely done.Gotta get out and
get a crate And get it back.
come on,jay!Once you
unclip it,Start heading back
come on,mike!
Jay has his Unclipped.He's headed back.
These crates weigh a lot!
Gotta get it on the platform.Go!
- go,go,go!
- troyzan,troyzan,take it!
Troyzan is down,Michael's back.Go!
Kim comes off the slide nicely.
Kim and michael heading out now.
go,troyzan,go,go,go.
Jay and troyzan have their Second
crate free,they're Heading back.
******we are very
tight Right off the bat.
good job,guys.
Go,cat!
come on,baby.
Michael and kim are Back.Go,sabrina!
Sabrina flies down the slide.
go,guys!
********
Kat still working on The clip.
Kim,sabrina and Michael
have taken over the lead Now.
push it!Push it!
Jay,troyzan,kat now
Fighting back for the lead.
We are neck and neck.Two
crates left for both tribes.
Go! Go!
Nice hard hit by christina.We
are still neck and neck.
let's go,guys,let's go!
Come on,guys,go!
Neck and neck now,Four crates in.
Chelsea,kat,troyzan,and
jay With a slight lead.
Huge reward on the
line.Everybody wants this.
Go,alicia!come on,alicia.
oh,my god.
- go,go,go,go!
- Go leif.
Leif flies off that slide
Face-first and he's up and Going.
Both tribes working on
their Fifth and final crate.
Jay,kat,chelsea alicia
and Troyzan in the lead.
Christina,sabrina,kim,Michael,leif
falling behind.
Start working our puzzle.
go.christina.
what is she doing?
Christina has already Gone
ahead,not helping at all.
Troyzan leading the way for his Tribe.
You have to get back to that
Platform before you can start Working.
Start working on the puzzle.
This is it.This is where it
is won or lot Of,right here.
- that's it.
- move those over here.
Christina,michael,Sabrina,leif
and kim trying to Get a plan.
Lot of people
talking.They look disorged.
go ahead.take your time.
Troyzan,kat,Chelsea,alicia and
jay,working Together very well.
Troyzan has a plan.
this doesn't go up
here.This doesn't match up.
he's right.Yeah,that doesn't fit.
right here,move that.
- yes!
- find this right here,an Outside one.
Troyzan thinks he has
Something going now.
this is it,this is tright Here.
Sabrina certain she's Right.
Christina's tribe Starting to get momentum.Are
they heading in the right Direction.
who cares what they're doing?
move it this way.
Yellow tribe is Getting close.
yes,yes.
Trying to keep their Excitement down.They
don't want to give anything Away.
sthoo it?
Both tribes very Close to solving it.
put it on the side.
I think we've got it.
Yellow tribe thinks They have it.
Yellow tribe is enjoying an
Afternoon barbecue reward!
we got it!We got it!We got it!
we got barbecue!Barbecue!Barbecue!
shut the ( bleep ) up.
barbecue!
Leif,christina,Sabrina,kim,michael,nice
Work.How's it feel?
amazing,amazing.My first reward.
I'm just ecstatic.I'm so happy.
My mouth is just drooling.
All right,you're Going to leave
here,be taken to The 7-up oasis.
I'm pretty sure you're
going to Enjoy it.
Congratulations.Come get
your reward and head Out.
thank you.
Jay,troiz an,kat,Alicia,chelsea,tarzan,got
Nothing for you.
Grab your stuff,head back to Camp.
when we first got to this
Amazing,beautiful 7-up oasis,
It was just shocking to
see how,Seriously,a resort.
oh,my god.
There was,like,potato salad,Potato
chips,pretzels,Cole slaw.
I would have been just been
Happy if it was plain steaks,
Hamburger and hot dogs and two
Pies but,hey,the more the Merrier.
It was amazing.
lord,we thank you just for
Allowing us to be here today
and Now we know what it feels like To be hungry
and so not only a Prayer and a tbrais for us
but a Prayer and a grace for those
all Over the world who are starving.
***
Thank you.
would you be offended if I
Took a bite out of this pie.
no.no.
I sprayed a little bit
of 7-up on the steak.
stope moaning.
the food is huge.I mean,I never
dreamt I would Feel so weak
so to be able to Think through my options and
sit Up and have my mind work feels Awesome.
this,like,the best meal.This
is exactly what I wanted.
you wanna come sit?
I can't stop eating this.
how far ahead are you Thinking?
- far.
- me,too.
what are you thinking?
I'd rather just have three
Really good people there and--
- me,you,and chelsea.
- yup.
that's what I think,sab.
it would piss me off to see
Somebody like mike up there.
me,too,it has to be all Girls.
yeah.
you can't beat this.How
would you beat this?
you know,we have toik make This
illusion as if we're still Salani.
- I know.
- I say mike.
okay.and that puts us six to Four.
I say we tail troy.
justice say mike is trying
to Get you out of here
if*****
we'll***
I like it.
we***
yeah.
I was trying to think through My options,and
I thought what Makes sense is to take out mike.
The girls are already in the Majority,
so if we can get a United front and come
together,We could start sending these Guys home.
I'm going to have to be careful,But if all
six girls vote Together and just go for it.
We can change the whole game.
****
A***
It*****
true.
We***
Should****
might as well.
what do you think,troy?
I think christina.
I agree.
we all know that christina is
Actually really,really Annoying,
however she's not as Big a threat.
We take out mike and we
are Taking out a threat.
He needs to be taken out asap.
I'm all about threats right Now.
I don't trust these girltz.
They want to send mike home but I'm going
to put that on the Back burner right now.
There are too many girls that Could hook
up and start knocking Out these guys.
they are*****
I'm*******
It's almost like a teacher
just Keeps smacking the student
make Sure they're doing the same Thing,making
sure they're on The same page here.
well,we just gotta decide
Before tomorrow comes.
hi,guys.look what we brute you guys?
- Look what we brought you.
- are you joking?
it's only soda.We could
take as much as we Wanted.
and it's cold.
have at it.
I was nervous before the
six Other guys came back.
What are they talking about
when They're on reward?
You know,are they talking Amongst each
other or do they Have,like,a new plan?
And now that we're back together I
really have to keep an eye on Those girls.
Kat made a suggestion that
mike May be the next to go.
So I have to make sure that
Sabrina,kim,and chelsea,
want To stick with the
salani group To the very end.
*******
look how windy it is
right Now.It's crazy.
it's going to get worse
Probably.Look at those clouds.
We've got something
moving in Really fast.
this is miserable.
Last night,it was raining and Windy
and the wall got blown off Our shelter.
Everything's wet.It's
just a big train wreck.
So we have to build our
shelter Up before tonight.
tarzan,don't reov any more Of this
stuff on this side of The wall.
We need everything we've got.
that was hanging there
Connected to nothing.
I haven't taken any intrinsic
Parts of this wall off,okay,Guys?
it sure looked that way.
like the most educate
people Have no common sense.
I know.
the wind has never been this Bad,and tarzan took
off part of Our bamboo wall to cut for Firewood.
When there's a whole stack
of Firewood for the fire.
why***
because somebody cut it
and Laid it there,okay?
I'm not that stupid.It's
not part of the wall.Okay?
Chelsea,you still thinking it's Part
of the wall and I stole a Piece of wall?
I'm over it.You've already
cut it up so it's No--
you shouldn't have attitude
When it's just hanging there.
I don't mind being accused
of Stuff when I'm wrong
but I don't Like being accused
of stuff when I'm right.
I'm not even talking about it Anymore.
well,good.
When you're around somebody you Sense
whether you're an irritant To them
and it seems chelsea's Been sort
of subliminally Harassing me.
it was an accusization.I don't like it.
You just let it go.
and I'm just a person if I Believe I've
been unfairly Maligned,I can't just take it.
I have to say something.
And I think I know why
she's Been unhappy with me.
I sense an aggravation with Me.
And I don't know if it's because You
you've had surgery and I'm a Plastic surgeon
and you don't Like your
plastic surgeon or Something,
but you-- you've been Negative towards
me since I've Come in contact with you.
tarzan took me off to the Side
and asked me if I didn't Like him
because I had a bad Experience
with my plastic Surgeon.
I mean,is this guy for real?
I can't believe he's
talking About my book job.
He's just--
he's crazy.
are you sure there
isn't a Deep-seated thing
because there Are people who have had
plastic Surgery and they hate their Surgeon.
no,that has nothing to do With anything.
It was just so annoying.
To me,it's,like,get tarzan
Out as fasts possible.
But it's a game where you
have To think with your head.
if you get that rope
over Here,I can pull it!
Leif,damn it,give me the rope!
as much as I can't stand
Tarzan,I think at this point
It's all about taking stronger People
out who could possibly be A threat.
And tarzan's not a threat at All.
So I hate to say it but I'm Thinking that
he needs to stick Around a little longer.
troy? I just thought
you should know That
mike is subtly planting the Seed in lots
of people's minds That you're going to win
and That,like,we can't
let you Make it that long,
and so I just Feel like we've
got to get mike Out of here
because he's one of The only people I think
that Could pull in christina and Alicia
and gets one more of us To vote and you're
going home And then we're al going home.
that pisses me off.
troyzan and I went this Morning
in the rain to get tree Mail
and I told him this whole Story about
hey,yesterday,mike Was throwing your name out There.
I think we need to take mike out First
and then we'll take up on The the girls.
I hate that guy.
So*****
I'm going
to try to--
but let's not tell him Because we need
him to feel Really sure that he's staying.
right.
this morning,I hear that Mike wants to take
me Out of the game,and that pitszs Me off.
He doesn't do jack
squat.He's just an idiot.
That guy--
rirks ks,me,man.
you always work all the Angles and
attack the challenges With fury.
Lose your balance or Concentration today
and tomorrow You may be on the jury.
mike,I've been worried
about Since day one,
and if mike wants To freaking vote
me out,he's Got another thing coming.
That guy should have
been gone On day one.
Come on in,guys!
You guys ready to get to
today's Immunity challenge?
yeah.
First things
first,Troyzan,I'll take it back.
- not for long.
- Thank you,sir.
"not for long" he says.
Once again,immunity
is back up For grabs.
For today's challenge,you will
Race across a ladder bridge
While mawferring bags of puzzle
Pieces along the twisting rope.
The first four to reach the Finish
line move on to the final Round
where you will use those Puzzle pieces to
solve a very Complicated "survivor" puzzle.
First one to get it right wins
Imimmunity,safe tonight at Tribal council,
guaranteed a one In continue
shot at the million Dollars.
Losers,tribal council,where
Somebody will be voted out.
We'll draw for spots
and we'll Get started.
All right,here we go.
For immunity and a one in 10
Shot at the money,survivors Ready?
Go!
You're working your way
across This ladder bridge
while you Mawfer the bags of
puzzle pieces Along the rope.
There's only one rule-- you fall
Off,you go back to the start.
Don't panic. We're
looking for four people.
To move on to the final round.
Right out of the gate,jay
is Moving quickly.
Troyzan doing a nice
job,Michael is in it.
Kim,chelsea are in it.
Rain starting to come
down now Right on cue.
Jay getting closer to the Finish.
It is jay,troyzan,michael and
Kim fighting for those four Spots.
Jay is across first.Jay
moving on to the finals.
Three spots left.Troyzan close.
Michael now hung up.He's been
at the same spot for a While.
Kim very close now.
Kim is across.Kim is moving on.
We're looking for two more Spots.
Alicia now in it.Tarzan is in it.
Michael and troyzan have
blown a Gigantic lead.
Opening the door for somebody
Else to slide through.
Troyzan finally figuring it out.
Troyzan is through.
We have one spot Left.Dig,people.
Chelsea falls off she's
got to Go back to the start.
Alicia moves on to the final.
yes!
Jay,troyzan,alicia,And kim moving on.
All right,here we go.It is
kim,alicia,troyzan,and Jay in the final round.
First one to solve this puzzle
Wins immunity.Survivors ready?
Go.
First step,you have to
open all The bags of pieces.
There are 60 pieces to this Puzzle.
60 blocks of wood.You have
to find the right home For.
this is too hard.
This will be a flat,Square
puzzle when you are done.
Lots of angles to work
with on These pieces.
It's going to take some time.
Alicia very excited.She
gets her first piece in.
There are a lot of pieces to be Placed.
You will know if the piece is
Right because it will line up Flat.
If it's not flat,it's not rig Right.
Kim looks to be very close.
Alicia very close now.
Troyzan is in on it.
Jay is dead last at this point.
Really taking his
time very Methodically.
I hate puzzles.
Troyzan and jay Trying to catch up,
but keep in Mind,the puzzle could
look Right until the very last piece,
- And then you find out Something's wrong.
- something's wrong.
So keep working on This,regardless
what the person Next to you is doing.
there you go,there you go.
Kim getting closer.
- what!
- One is not right.
Now she's got to get it
out,Find the right spot.
That's opening the door for
Troyzan to get back in on this.
Jay is suddenly back in this Now.
He was dead last before.
Everybody's in this challenge Now.
Alicia is getting closer.
Does alicia have it?
No.Alicia has a piece
sticking up.She's not right.
Jay now getting closer.
Could jay pull this huge
Come-from-behind victory out? Right here.
- there you go,there you go.
- okay,come on,go.
There you go.
- Kim getting closer.
- good job!
It's kim and jay.
Jay places another
piece.He's getting closer.
Kim down to her last piece.
Jay down to his last piece.
Kim,no!
Out of nowhere,jay wins Immunity!
slow and steady wins the Race,baby.
amazing.
Jay,come on over.
jay bird.
You were dead last For most of
that puzzle part of The challenge,
out of the blue,Came from
behind,immunity is Yours.Safe tonight.
As for the rest of you,one
of You going home tonight.
Grab your stuff,head back to Camp.I'll
see you tonight at tribal Council.Congrats.
****
******
Nice***
yeah***
- nice comeback!
- yeah.
tonight,I had the immunity Necklace
around my neck,so I Feel safe.
I definitely think that since
we Knocked jonas off last time,
you Know,I think it's just a
safe Vote to knock off a girl.
So we're going to send christina Home.
That keeps the old salani
Members going strong
and sends An old manono member home as
Well as evens out the guys Versus the girls.
It***
with mike? oh,yeah.
I***
right now,I'm straddling to Alliances.
I have an all-women alliance and I have nigh
salani alliance with Troy,jake jay,and mike.
But now I feel like it's time For
the girls to take over this Game.
I know that chelsea and the
Girls will be on board with That,
and troirk he's blinded
by His dislike of mike.
So I'm using troy to
send mike Home tonight.
I didn't talk to jay did,You?
I didn't talk to anyone.
I'm sure he's fine with it.
My concern is if jay find
out What's really going on
because If jay gets suspicious and gets To troy
and troy gets nervous That could be trouble.
I still have to keep my
options Open,and who knows?
I may need those guys
for Another vote or two.
jay.What do you think about
getting Rid of mike tonight?
to be honest,I'm scared of Y'all girls.
If y'all get rid of
him,y'all Get rid of me next.
that's not necessarily true.
not necessarily
true.That's real promising.
anybody got any input
while I'm sitting here?
Or are we gonna scramble
one on One and do this?
I was sitting in the shelter and Chelsea looked
at me and asked If I was going to send mike home
And it just really shocked me That she would
say this in front Of alicia and christina.
Because****
You're supposed to be part of my Alliance and you're
talking like This in front of two other People.
I don't like that plan.
I have to be careful with these Girls because
fidon't go along With them and they vote out Mike,
they might very well come After me.
jay was like,"I don't trust That because
that means I could Be the next to go
and y'all are Going to have
an all-girls thing Going on."
that's what I thought.
apparently,chelsea literally Sat there
in the shelter in Front of the two girls
that are Not supposed to be a part of our
Alliance and asked jay to vote For mike.
That's asinine.
We need to keep troy and jay
Thinking it's salani to the end.
And now it's kind of become a Huge mess.
So I'm not exactly sure how
this Is about to go down.
we cannot send a girl home Tonight.
what are we going to tell Mike? Mike
is going to ask me who We're voting for.
hopefully we can be cool
About it and not get panicky.
mike just went for a walk.
He's going to blow this camp up.
I'm going.
pure insanity.
what are y'all thinking?
I don't know.Nobody's talked to me.
check this out.We were sitting
back there,Chomping on popcorn--
let's do christina.
I***
they're all in the same boat.
So***
and then next time do guy and
Girl.Then the manono tribe is gone.
I mean****
And***
I'm not saying I don't trust
Y'all but I'm just saying
I Don't have a good vibe going on.
jay,you know,he's really Nervous,but
my alliance is Sticking together
and for every Person that's not in
an alliance It's your turn to go.
**********
There's no scrambling.Everybody
can just relax and go To tribal.
As long as it doesn't happen to
You,you know,then you're okay.
But I could say that now and Have my tribe
blindside me but I Just tonight see that happening.
I***
I'm just saying,somes Going to be different
after Tonight so what we have to do Right now
is decide it if we're Gog lay
down tonight and vote Christina owf
or if we're about To make our move because this
is Never going to be the same if we Do this.
I'm torn over what to do because It's a huge
move to take out the Guys in our alliance,
and,Unfortunately,jay freaked out.
So are we gonna,like,cause a Major uproar,go
with the Women's alliance,and vote off Mike?
Or do we vote off
christina,Keep salani together?
So we're going to have to
make a Choice and go with it.
Whatever happens is going
to Change the whole game.
We'll now bring in The
first member of our jury.
Jonas,voted out at the
last Tribal council.
I want to start by asking one Question
looking for a truthful Response.
Who here tonight is genuinely Worried
that it is them going Home tonight?
Nobody.Thinks it's them tonight.
Amazing.
So what it really means is
there Are a lot of alliances
and all Of them feel very
soland I had Very loyal.
Tarzan,do you get a kick
out of The fact that nobody,
including Yourself,thinks
they're in Trouble tonight,
and yet we know In just a few moments
somebody Will be out of this game for Good.
it means somebody has been Very ggd
at deceiving is what it Means,jeff.
Troyzan if you got Blindsided by your
alliance Would it really blow you away?
yeah,I feel like if I got
Blindsideide didn't bring my Bags,
so,yeah,I would be Shocked.
Kim,do you feel the Same way?
it would blow me away.
How about you,Chelsea.
same.
christina.
Mike,same question.
it would definitely blow me Away.
It would be a complete surprise.
Kim,where is the Confidence coming from
that Nobody tonight thinks it's them.
I think there are people that
Think they're part of an Alliance
and that's where the
Confusion is setting in.
We all did have our first Alliances
but then we had time To develop new
relationships When we switched tribes
so I Think so you always
have to keep Your options open
and know when To stick with a plan,too.
Chelsea,that's a Really
carefully crafted answer.
I think in a way you want to Be
aligned with more than two Groups,
maybe you want to be
Aligned with three groups,
and Just see which one has more Trust
and keep yourself with the Majority.
So maybe it's good to have more Options.
Alicia,does that add A whole other
dimension that you Now have 11 people experk
Because the lines aren't really
Clear,I have to keep track of Everybody,
because anybody could Be coming for me?
I definitely agree.
I feel like right now,we still
Don't know who is on whose side.
And it's going to take a couple Of
tribal councils to figure it Out,
and see who is loyal to who And
who's going to be the one on Top.
Christina,six women,Five men,is there any
talk that It might still be men versus Women?
I'm sure,yeah.But there's also
the question of The new alliances
that they Build from the salani
tribe and The manono tribe.
When we switched.
right.And I think that's why a lot of People
aren't really sure if They are going or not.
Tarzan.
well,I hate to say it,jeff,But
we're all just playing you
Because we know how
important This night is.
What needs to be said is the Allegianceallegiances
that wered Prior to coming here
one would Think would be relatively
firm And not so wishy-washy,
and if We reveal too much
it will ruin The whole thing
so the game is Afoot and that's why
we remain Exwigz.It's our best bet.
And,therefore,you're being Played.
So I'm being played Tonight.
you bet,you're being
played.I'm sure you sense That.
Kat,we've got a Million-dollar
game on the line,
We're about to vote and
everyone Is laughing at tarzan.
It's so funny.Everybody
is in a good mood.
it's because his rant
t Rantic is so tarzan.
It's like a boom!And you're
like what just happ Happen.
Did I get tar swrand Tonight?
you got tarzanned.
Michael,when tarzan
Says,"I'm being played,"
clearly it's everybody
except At least one person.
there's at least two Alliances,but
then at the same Time,
you don't know who is Exactly
with who because Everybody talks.
As far as me and my alliance,I Mean,I don't talk
much around Camp but when I do I remain Cool.
That's how I am as a person.My
alliance,I think is strong.8
With that,I will say To you,tarzan,though
you think I'm being played.
I'm pretty sure one of you guys Are being
played,and we're Going to find out who it is.
Cannot vote for jay.He
has the immunity necklace.
Everybody else is fair
game.It is time to vote.
Tarzan,you're up.
***
I'll go tally the Votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity Idol and you
want to play it,Now would be the time to do so.
Okay,once the votes are
read,The decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked To leave
the tribal council area Immediately.
I'llei'll read the votes.
First vote,christina.
Two votes christina.
Tarzan.
Tarzan.Two votes
christina,two votes Tarzan.
Mike.
Two votes mike,two votes
Christina,two votes tarzan.
Mike. That's three votes mike.
Mike. That's four votes mike.
Two votes christina,two votes Tarzan.
Eighth person voted out,and the
Second member of our jury,mike.
That's five,that's enough.You
need to bring me your torch.
Mike,the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well,you came in here tonight
Completely confident it wasn't You,
and yet,three of you Received votes.
If that doesn't shake the Confidence
of this group,Nothing will.
Grab your torches,head
back to Camp.Good night.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-  Proudly Presents
Sync:Å£±¼ÉÁÉÁºÙ
Next time on Survivor.
The women are in control of the Game.
these girls it going
to knock Us all out.
sth***
The men fight back.
the next four votes are Coming your way.
who are you voting for?
they're going to get the
Full-on switcha radio.
We***
Are***
**********
going into it at some point
It would be byes versus girls,
And unfortunately,it started Tonight.
I came out of the gates too hat,I
talked to the women all Individually,
and I thought I Had a good thing with
them,but,Apparently,un,you can't trust Anybody,
*********