Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
AFTER A ROUGH START FOR THE
WOMEN'S TRIBE... WOMEN WIN THEIR
THIRD STRAIGHT CHALLENGE!
MOMENTUM HAD FINALLY SWUNG THEIR
WAY.
BACK AT CAMP, LEIF LEAKED
INFORMATION TO THE ENEMY
ALLIANCE.
WHEN.
WHEN COLTON SAID TO VOTE TO
YOU, I DIDN'T REALLY WANT THAT,
YOU KNOW?
Jeff: AND QUICKLY FOUND HIS
NAME ON COLTON'S HIT LIST,
ALONGSIDE BILL.
I TOLD YOU TO PICK A SIDE AND
YOU PICKED THE WRONG SIDE.
Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE...
CHEATER!
KISS MY ASS.
Jeff: ... THE WOMEN
SUFFERED A DEVASTATING LOSS.
MEN WIN IMMUNITY!
BUT IT WAS THE MEN'S TRIBE WHO
LOST THEIR MIND.
LISTEN YOU LITTLE STUCK-UP
BRAT, I'M TELLING YOU...
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I WANT HIM GONE.
Jeff: COLTON WANTED TO GET
RID OF BILL.
WE CAN GIVE THE GIRLS
IMMUNITY AND GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL AND VOTE OUT BILL.
I'M LIKE WHAT IN THE WORLD IS
GOING ON?
I'M COMPLETELY BUM-PUZZLED RIGHT
NOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF
THIS.
Jeff: EVERYONE GAVE IN, NOT
WANTING TO GO AGAINST THE
MAJORITY.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL COLTON
CONTINUED HIS ATTACK ON BILL.
HE'S A STRUGGLING STANDUP
COMIC.
LIKE, GET A REAL JOB.
ME BEING POOR, THAT'S JUST MY
LIFE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SUGAR COAT
IT.
I DON'T ASSOCIATE WITH PEOPLE
LIKE THAT IN THE REAL WORLD AND
I'M SURE AS HELL NOT GOING TO
ASSOCIATE WITH PEOPLE LIKE THAT
OUT HERE.
Jeff: IN THE END, COLTON
GOT HIS WAY.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: ONE WORLD," BILL.
AND NOW THE MEN AND WOMEN ARE
EVEN AT SEVEN AND IT'S ANYONE'S
GAME.
14 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
IT FEELS LIKE IT TODAY.
YOU GUYS ARE HUNKERED DOWN
TOGETHER, MAN.
TROY, WHOSE IDEA WAS IT TO
GIVE UP THE IDOL?
GIVE THE IDOL BACK?
COLTON'S.
BUT YOU KNOW IN SOME GUYS HEADS
THEY WERE GOING HOME.
I DIDN'T WANT TO AGREE WITH IT
BUT IT'S A GROUP THING SO I
DON'T KNOW.
WE REALLY SHOULD HAVE SIX
PEOPLE ON THIS TRIBE BUT WE HAVE
SEVEN.
THE GUYS ARE MUCH MORE OF A MESS
THAN WHAT WE THOUGHT, YOU KNOW?
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO QUESTION
THEIR NONSENSE OVER THERE.
I'M HAPPY WE HAVE SEVEN AND THE
GIRLS ARE STICKING TOGETHER ON
THIS ONE.
IF WE'RE GOING TO STICK AS A
TRIBE OF ALL GIRLS, WE NEED TO
BE SEVEN GOING IN STRONG.
WE HAVE TO STICK TOGETHER
BECAUSE WE DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
HECK THESE GUYS ARE THINKING.
IT'S LIKE... I MEAN, IT'S CRAZY
STUFF THAT'S HAPPENING OVER
THERE.
YES.
WE NEED TO WIN IT.
YEAH.
THE GUYS MESSED UP BIG TIME.
I'M EXCITED.
I REALLY WANT TO WIN.
IF WE COME IN STRONG SEVEN
WE'RE GOING TO BLOW THEM AWAY.
WE'RE GOING TO BEAT THEM TODAY
IN OUR CHALLENGE.
THEY ARE SO DUMB.
THEY HANDED US A MILLION
DOLLARS.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
YES, SIR.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BEFORE WE
GET TO THE CHALLENGE, YOU CAN
DROP YOUR BUFFS, BECAUSE WE ARE
SWITCHING TRIBES.
NO WAY!
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: TAKE THEM OFF AND
DROP THEM AT YOUR FEET.
OH, BOY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO TAKE
THIS THING OFF.
HERE WE GO.
Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING
TO WORK.
IT WILL BE A RANDOM SWITCH.
YOU'RE EACH GOING TO DRAW AN
EGG.
WHEN I TELL YOU TO, YOU'LL SMASH
IT AGAINST YOUR BODY.
TAKEN A EGG.
DON'T DO ANYTHING WITH IT YET.
WHATEVER COLOR COMES OUT WILL
DETERMINE WHAT TRIBE YOU ARE ON.
CAN WE EAT THIS THING?
Jeff: I'M GOING TO COUNT
YOU DOWN.
HERE WE GO, THREE, TWO, ONE,
SMASH.
OH!
Jeff: IF YOU ARE BLUE, YOU
ARE A SALANI MEMBER.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BLUE MAT.
IF YOU ARE ORANGE, YOU ARE A
MANONO MEMBER.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE ORANGE MAT.
HELLO, GENTLEMEN.
LADIES.
HEY!
Jeff: KIM, DID YOUR TRIBE
JUST GET BETTER OR WORSE?
THIS COULD HAVEN'T GONE
BETTER FOR US.
THEY HAVE ALL THE MUSCLE.
(LAUGHTER).
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MICHAEL,
SABRINA, KAT, JAY, KIM, CHELSEA,
TROYZAN, YOU ARE THE NEW SALANI
TRIBE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
TARZAN, COLTON, CHRISTINA,
ALICIA, MONICA, LEIF AND JONAS,
YOU ARE THE NEW MANONO TRIBE.
MEN AND WOMEN ARE NO MORE.
MANONO ON THREE, ONE, TWO,
THREE, MANONO!
WE GOT IT.
WE GOT THIS.
Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR FIRST REWARD CHALLENGE
AS NEW TRIBES?
(APPLAUSE)
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
WORK TOGETHER.
TEAMS OF FOUR WILL CARRY A LARGE
BUCKET TO A WATER TOWER WHERE
YOU WILL FILL IT.
ON YOUR WAY BACK YOU WILL WORK
TOGETHER TO PLUG THE HOLES THAT
ARE LEAKING OUT ALL THE WATER
YOU JUST COLLECTED.
WHEN YOU GET TO YOUR FINISHED
PLATFORM, YOU'LL DUMP THE WATER
IN THE CONTAINER AND HEAD BACK
OUT.
FIRST TRIBE TO FILL THEIR
CONTAINER AND RAISE THEIR FLAG
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING?
YES!
YES, SIR!
Jeff: THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL TAKE BACK TO CAMP WITH
THEM...
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: PEANUT BUTTER AND
JELLY SANDWICHES.
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY?
Jeff: AND COFFEE.
WITH SUGAR!
Jeff: IN ADDITION, THE
WINNING TRIBE EARN IT IS RIGHT
TO CONTINUE LIVING AT THE "ONE
WORLD" BEACH.
OH, MY GOSH!
Jeff: THE LOSING TRIBE WILL
BE SENT TO A NEW BEACH WHERE YOU
MUST CREATE A NEW WORLD.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: WE ARE SEVEN ON
SEVEN, NOBODY'S SITTING OUT.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
THE FIRST REWARD CHALLENGE WITH
NEW TRIBES.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
VERY SIMPLE CHALLENGE.
FILL YOUR BUCKET WITH WATER AND
GET BACK AS QUICKLY AS YOU CAN.
THE CATCH IS YOUR BUCKET HAS
HOLES.
LET'S GO!
COME ON!
Jeff: A LITTLE BIT OF
STRATEGY, HOW MUCH TIME DO YOU
SPEND PUTTING WATER IN YOUR
BUCKET BEFORE DIMINISHING RETURN
SCENARIO?
OH, MONICA TAKES A HARD FALL AND
LOSES A LOT OF WATER!
COME ON!
Jeff: MONICA GOES DOWN
AGAIN LOSING MORE WATER!
SALANI HEADING BACK NOW.
CHRISTINA, ALEASE KWRARBGS
MONICA AND COLTON NOW FOR
MANONO.
IT'S JAY, TROYZAN, MICHAEL AND
KAT FOR SALANI.
CAN YOU PULL HARDER?
NO.
Jeff: MANONO HEADING BACK
WITH MORE WATER.
COME ON, GUYS, YOU GOT IT!
Jeff: SALANI HEADING BACK.
NO LEAK, YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
VERY LITTLE LEAK.
Jeff: MANONO LOOKS LIKE
THEY HAVE A VERY FULL BUCKET
THIS TIME.
A TON OF WATER FOR SALANI.
SALANI NOW WITH A BIT OF A LEAD
IN THE WATER.
ONE MORE BUCKET COULD DO IT FOR
EITHER TRIBE.
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY
SANDWICHES, COFFEE AND STAYING
AT A HOME YOU HAVE WORKED SO
HARD TO BUILD, LOSERS GO TO A
NEW BEACH WITH NOTHING.
LET'S GO.
KEEP GOING!
Jeff: MANONO HEADING BACK.
TARZAN, COVER THOSE HOLES!
THIS IS IT.
GO.
Jeff: COULD THIS BE ENOUGH
TO WIN IT RIGHT HERE?
CLOSE BUT NO.
THIS COULD DO IT FOR SALANI
(SCREAMING)
SALANI WINS REWARD!
Jeff: COLTON, GIVE ME A
HARD TRUTH ABOUT THIS NEW
DIVISION OF TRIBES RIGHT NOW?
WELL, LOOK AT THEM AND LOOK
AT US.
IT'S LIKE GREEK GODS VERSUS
PEASANTS.
OH, EXCUSE ME.
I'M JUST KIDDING!
PARDON ME, MY FRIEND.
FAR FROM FROM A PEASANT, MY
FRIEND.
NO, VILLAGE PEOPLE.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE'S HOW
IT'S GOING TO WORK.
SALANI YOU'LL GO BACK TO THE
"ONE WORLD" BEACH.
TAKE YOUR PEANUT BUTTER AND
JELLY AND COFFEE WITH YOU.
YOU GUYS ONE FISHING GEAR, YOU
WILL HAVE THE OTHER FISHING
GEAR.
IT'S A BRAND-NEW START.
MANONO HERE'S A MAP TO YOUR NEW
HOME.
SALANI, COME GET YOUR REWARD,
HEAD BACK.
ENJOY IT.
ALL RIGHT, MANONO, TAKE YOUR
MAP, HEAD OUT AND GET STARTED
BUILDING YOUR NEW WORLD.
GOOD LUCK.
WE WENT TO THE REWARD
CHALLENGE TODAY AND WHEN WE
PICKED THE EGG I SAID LORD,
PLEASE LET IT BE THE SAME COLOR
AS KIM.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED.
WELCOME TO OUR HOME, GUYS.
I SMASHED IT IT WAS BLUE; SHE
WAS BLUE; CHELSEA WAS BLUE.
THAT'S, LIKE, OUR FIRST THREE IN
OUR ALLIANCE.
THEN I SAW KAT AND I WAS JUST
LIKE OH, MY GOD!
IS THIS REALLY REAL?
MAYBE A SLICE WITH PEANUT
BUTTER AND JELLY ON IT?
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS AMAZING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE...
OH, MY GOD.
...FOUR GIRLS WITHIN THE
FIVE-GIRL ALLIANCE ON THE NEW
TRIBE.
PRICELESS.
WHEN I CRACKED THAT EGG AND I
SAW ORANGE AND I LOOKED AROUND
AND JAY WAS COVERED IN BLUE AND
TROY WAS BLUE AND I LOOKED OVER
AND KIM HAD BLUE AND SABRINA HAD
BLUE AND I JUST THOUGHT... BEEP.
ALL RIGHT, WE GOT ROPES, WE
GOT WATER HOLDERS.
A LOT MORE POTS AND PANS.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE
FINE.
I KNOW.
EVERYTHING IS GOING TO BE
FINE.
WE GOT A BETTER HOUSE.
IT'S GOING TO BE SO MUCH
BETTER HERE.
THIS IS A BETTER PLACE.
SOFT SAND.
NOT ONLY DID I GET ON A TRIBE
WITH PEOPLE THAT I DON'T WANT TO
BE ON A TRIBE WITH, I GOT ON A
TRIBE WITH PEOPLE WHO SUCK!
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
COMPETE WITH THEM IN ANYTHING,
YOU KNOW?
THEY'RE GREEK GODS.
THEY'RE GOING TO DOMINATE US IN
CHALLENGES.
THEY'RE EATING PEANUT BUTTER AND
JELLY SANDWICHES.
THEY'RE GETTING STRONGER THAN
THEY ALREADY ARE.
OH, MY GOD, WE ARE GOING TO
BE THE LAUGHING STOCK.
WE ARE NOT GOING TO WIN.
I ALREADY KNOW WE'RE NOT GOING
TO WIN.
EVEN IF THE GIRLS DIDN'T HAVE
THE GUYS ON THEIR TEAM AT SALANI
THEY'D STILL PROBABLY KICK OUR
BUTTS.
THAT'S HOW SAD THAT IS.
THE PRINCE AND THE PRINCESS.
WILL YOU BE MY PRINCE?
WILL YOU BE MY PRINCESS?
EVEN THOUGH I CAN BE A COMPLETE
AND TOTAL EVIL PERSON, I KNOW
HOW TO RELATE TO PEOPLE.
I KNOW HOW TO CHARM PEOPLE.
I KNOW HOW TO TELL THEM WHAT
THEY WANT TO HEAR.
I KNOW HOW TO GET THEM ON MY
SIDE.
I WANT TO GIVE MY LOYALTY TO
YOU GUYS?
YOU PROMISE?
PINKY PROMISE?
I DON'T WANT TO GET BLINDSIDED.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET
BLINDSIDED.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST.
BUT WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER.
WE HAVE TO ACT LIKE WE'RE A
UNIFIED TRIBE.
WHO I HAVE BEEN WITH SINCE
DAY ONE?
I'VE WANTED TO BE WITH THE
GIRLS.
COOL.
I'M GOING TO GO BACK.
SO Y'ALL ARE GOOD?
I'M TELLING CHRISTINA WHAT SHE
WANTS TO HEAR.
I'M YOUR BEST FRIEND, YOU HAVE
TO TRUST ME.
THAT'S SO SHE'LL GIVE ME
INFORMATION.
I WANT EVERYBODY TO TRUST ME SO
THEY'LL GIVE ME INFORMATION.
YOU'RE NOT WITH THE GUYS ARE
YOU?
A PINKY PROMISE.
I PINKY PROMISE.
DEAL, WE GOT THREE GIRLS AND
YOU.
WE'RE SET.
HONEY, I'M NOT A LIAR.
OKAY, OKAY.
I KNOW.
I WON'T LEAVE YOU NOW.
DON'T FORGET, WHO'S YOUR MAMA?
COLTON JOINED US AND I FELT LIKE
OKAY, THERE'S POWER IN NUMBERS
BUT I'M NOT SURE.
I HOPE YOU'RE STILL WITH US.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT THE PUPPET
MASTER MANIPULATOR AND THAT YOU
REALLY AND TRULY AREN'T WITH THE
GUYS AND US GIRLS ARE GOING DOWN
ONE, TWO, THREE.
AND I FEEL LIKE I'M THE
STRONGEST OF THE THREE GIRL
WHICH IS WOULD MEAN IT WOULD BE
ME FIRST.
JUST ONE RIGHT ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THAT ROCK.
WHERE?
I DON'T SEE.
THERE'S ONE RIGHT HERE, TOO.
WHOA!
DID YOU GET IT?
YUP.
OH, MY GOD!
JUST POKE THEM IN THE CENTER.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S FOUR.
THIS WILL BE OUR LUNCH WITH P.B.
AND J.
WE'LL EAT SO GOOD.
NICE DINNER RICE AND MORE CRABS.
SCREW FISHING.
GUYS, GATHER AROUND FOR THIS
LOAD.
STAY THERE!
SABRINA, CLOSE IN OVER THERE.
MIKE, PUT YOUR STUFF DOWN AND
CLOSE IN.
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
WHERE IS HE?
GOT HIM!
YES!
(SCREAMING)
TODAY HAS BEEN JUST
FANTASTIC.
IT REMINDED ME BACK IN 1979 WHEN
I PLAYED CORNERBACK FOR THE
CENTRAL VALLEY BEARS.
WHICH WAY IS HE GOING?
BOOM.
I MEAN, IT WAS TOTAL INSTINCT.
THAT WAS IT.
GAME OVER.
SORRY, CHICKEN, YOU LOSE.
(LAUGHS)
HOLY CRAP!
WE GOT MORE.
OH, MY GOD!
WE CAUGHT A ROOSTER TODAY.
MIKE AND CHELSEA GOT FOUR HUGE
CRABS.
GOOD DAY OF HUNTING.
(APPLAUSE)
SALANI, BABY.
SALANI.
IT'S LIKE THE GODS SAID "COME
TOGETHER AND I WILL PROVIDE YOU
WITH WHAT YOU WANT."
IT'S BEEN WILD!
HAY, TROY, DO WE HAVE ANY
SPACE BETWEEN US AND THE REST OF
THE PEOPLE IN THE OCEAN?
MIKE AND KAT ARE IN THE
OCEAN.
THAT'S IT.
WE WERE THINKING GOING INTO A
MERGE SITUATION WE WANT TO MAKE
SURE YOU HAVE A SOLID FOUR OR
FIVE PEOPLE.
THE BOY IN THE OCEAN IS NOT ONE
OF THEM.
FINE WITH ME, DUDE.
YOU KNOW ME.
I THINK IT'S SALANI VERSUS
MANONO RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T THINK IT'S MEN VERSUS
WOMEN AND IF IT WAS WE WOULD BE
ON THE OUTS BECAUSE WE'RE DOWN A
MAN AS FAR AS OUR TRIBE GOES.
THEY HAVE ONE MORE GIRL.
I DON'T MIND AT ALL WORKING WITH
THESE WOMEN.
I THINK I CAN TRUST THEM.
I WANT TO GET TO KNOW THEM
BETTER AND SEE WHERE THEIR HEADS
ARE AT.
WHAT'S CHELSEA LIKE?
CHELSEA'S GREAT.
SHE HASN'T BEEN PLAYING
STRATEGY.
SHE'S JUST KIND OF... SHE'S
GAME.
I TRUST HER.
ALL RIGHT.
WHATEVER MERGE SITUATION
HAPPENS.
LET'S INTERMINGLE, WEAVE OUR WAY
INTO IT.
AND WHEN IT COMES TIME TO
VOTE WE HAVE TO TELL EACH OTHER
WHAT'S GOING DOWN AND MAKE SURE
THAT IT GOES NOT TOWARDS ANY ONE
OF US AND PRETTY SOON WE'RE IN
THE MAJORITY AND IT DOESN'T
MATTER ANYMORE.
THIS HAS BEEN MY THING ALL
ALONG.
I'M TRYING TO KEEP MY OPTIONS
OPEN SO IF STICKING WITH THE
GIRLS WORKS BEST FOR ME I'LL
STICK WITH THE GIRLS.
AND IF WE GET TO THE MERGE AND
DON'T HAVE THE NUMBERS, TROY AND
JAY ARE MY ALLIANCE ALL THE WAY.
I CAN'T GET OVER HOW THIS COULD
NOT HAVE GONE ANY BETTER FOR ME
AND HOW MUCH FUN I'M HAVING
DOING THIS.
ANYBODY ELSE WANT TO CHEW ON
THAT?
OH, YEAH.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE
HARD AND A GRIND AND I KNOW IT
WILL HAVE ITS MOMENTS BUT THIS
IS NOT ONE OF THEM.
THIS IS A GOOD TIME.
I DON'T LIKE THIS JOB.
I DON'T LIKE HAVING TO TRUST
PEOPLE THAT I DON'T TRUST.
WELL, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
TRY TO TRUST THEM.
OH, I TRUST MONICA.
YOU DON'T TRUST CHRISTINA?
NO.
NOT AT ALL.
I DON'T, EITHER.
I'M ALMOST THINKING-- DON'T
YOU DARE SAY ANYTHING TO MONICA
ABOUT THIS, YOU SWEAR?
SWEAR.
WE NEED TO GET OUT CHRISTINA
FIRST.
WE NEED FOUR, THOUGH.
I'M TELLING YOU, WE MIGHT BE
SAFER WITH TARZAN AND JONAS.
I'M TELLING YOU.
NO.
THAT'S UNSTABLE.
UH-UH.
THAT'S WHY YOU GUYS HAD ALL THAT
CRAZY STUFF GOING DOWN.
LEAVE IT AS IT IS.
THE GIRLS ARE LOYAL.
YOU GUYS ARE THE ONES WHO ARE
CRAZY.
I DON'T CONSIDER COLTON AS A GUY
SO I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE FOUR
WOMEN AGAINST THREE GUYS.
BUT COLTON'S CRAZY.
HE REALLY WANTS CHRISTINA OUT
BUT I NEED TO KEEP MY WOMEN HERE
AND GET RID OF THE GUYS SO THAT
WHEN WE MERGE I'M STILL THERE.
OR... OR AT LEAST KEEP MY NAME
IN THE MIX.
SO WHAT'S THE STORY BETWEEN
YOU AND ALICIA.
I'M JUST TALKING TO HER.
YOU'RE IN GOOD WITH HER.
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
I'M STICKING WITH THE GUYS,
HONESTLY.
I CAN'T AFFORD TO GO WITH THESE
WOMEN.
WHILE WE'RE WORKING BUSTING
OUR ASS BUILDING A SHELTER,
COLTON IS DOING THE SAME THING!
HE'S JUST SITTING ON HIS ASS
TALKING TO ALICIA.
I'M LIKE WHAT IS GOING ON?
HOW... HOW DOES HE GET AWAY WITH
THIS?
I... IT JUST... IT'S... I NEVER
THOUGHT TO PLAY THAT GAME.
IT'S BRILLIANT.
THEY HAVE TO THINK I'M THEIR
FOURTH.
BUT I'M NOT.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST ME.
DON'T SCAM ME BRO.
FIST BUMP, I'M NOT.
SERIOUSLY.
I PROMISE YOU.
HALF OF ME BELIEVES HIM, HALF
OF ME IS LIKE... HE'S LIKE "I'M
SUCH A GIRL."
WHAT IS THAT?
CHRISTINA'S GOING FIRST?
YES, JUST REMEMBER TO WRITE
HER NAME DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD DEAL?
OKAY, SWEET ENOUGH.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE COLTON'S
JUST RUNNING THE SHOW ON BOTH
SIDES WITH THE WOMEN AND THE MEN
BUT IT WOULD BE RICK RIDICULOUS
FOR ME NOT TO THINK HE'S
ALIGNING WITH THE WOMEN RIGHT
NOW.
OH, MY GOD!
SABRINA FINDS THE IMMUNITY
IDOL BUT IT'S NOT FOR OUR TRIBE.
SHE GETS TO PLAY IT FOR ONE OF
THE GUYS.
NOBODY REALLY HAD THE GIRLS'
IDOL AND SOMETHING MAP ISED FOR
ME AND I THOUGHT I'M LITERALLY
GOING TO FIND THIS RIGHT NOW.
IT'S OUT HERE SOMEWHERE.
I WALKED ALL AROUND THE GUY'S
SIDE LOOKED AT EVERY TREE,
NOTHING, NOTHING.
I WAS GETTING DISCOURAGED AND
SAID, LORD, PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
FINALLY.
I JUST FOUND THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
IT FEELS AMAZING.
I'VE LOOKED SO HARD SO I HAD TO
LITERALLY REACH IN THERE AND
FEEL IT.
I JUST FOUND THE IMMUNITY IDOL
AND IT'S IN MY CROTCH.
YOU'RE LYING.
I'M NOT.
SHUT UP!
OKAY, ARE YOU READY?
HOLY COW!
DAMN!
AS SOON AS I FOUND THE IDOL
I'VE KIND OF BEEN THINKING I
MIGHT KEEP IT TO MYSELF BUT AS I
WAS TRYING TO GRAB IT AND GET IT
I THOUGHT THERE'S NO ONE I TRUST
IN THIS GAME MORE THAN CHELSEA
IF I'M GOING TO DO THIS WITH
ANYONE IT WILL BE WITH HER SO I
DECIDED TO LET HER IN ON IT.
NOW THAT WE HAVE THIS AND WE
CAN LITERALLY... LIKE, THIS
COULD BE A GAME CHANGER WHERE WE
TAKE THE NUMBERS.
NO ONE CAN KNOW, NOT A WORD OF
IT.
HELL NO.
AND WE NEED TO BE CAREFUL
THEY DON'T SEE US AS A PAIR
BECAUSE THE OTHER ONE WOULD
NEVER HAVE AN IDEA.
WE JUST NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT
WE HAVE OUR ALLIANCE WITH AS
MANY PEOPLE AS POSSIBLE.
THIS IS AWESOME.
PULL THE THING.
PULL IT!
SLOWLY, SLOWLY.
WHAT ARE YOU?
(SCREAMING)
WE GOT A CHICKEN!
OH, MY GOD!
WE ARE SO FED!
LOOK AT THAT!
WE'RE SO AWESOME, GUYS!
HOW'D HE GET OUT?
THESE PEOPLE SUCK AT
"SURVIVOR."
I MEAN, LET'S JUST BE HONEST.
THEY SUCK AT "SURVIVOR."
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO LOSE THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES REGARDLESS.
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE A CHANCE
IN HELL OF WINNING.
I GUESS WE SHOULD HAVE
CHECKED THE SIDES OF THE COOP.
THAT'S EMBARRASSING.
I THINK MONICA AND CHRISTINA
ARE BOTH ON THE OUTS BUT MONICA
HAS WAY MORE POWER THAN
CHRISTINA.
CHRISTINA HAS NO FRIENDS ON THAT
OTHER TRIBE AND WHEN WE MERGE IF
MONICA'S AT THAT MERGE IT'S
GOING TO BE BAD.
IF CHRISTINA'S THERE, IT'S NOT A
BIG DEAL.
SHE'S GOING TO BE EASY TO GET
RID OF.
HERE'S THE THING I NEED TO KNOW
FROM YOU.
THIS IS JUST ME AND YOU TALKING,
OKAY?
OKAY.
MONICA'S A HELL OF A LOT
SCARIER THAN CHRISTINA.
AGREED.
BUT MONICA HAS TO GO NEXT.
SO MONICA AND THEN WHO'S NEXT
AFTER MONICA?
CHRISTINA.
IF YOU...
BUT YOU'RE ASKING... I'M JUST
SAYING, YOU HAVE TO SEE IT MY
WAY.
I SEE IT YOUR WAY.
YOU ARE ASKING ME TO TRUST A
WHOLE OTHER TRIBE...
NO, I'M NOT.
I'M ASKING YOU TO TRUST ME.
ONE PERSON WHO CAN CONTROL THOSE
GUYS.
OKAY.
DEAL.
ALL RIGHT?
I JUST HAD TO CONVINCE ALICIA I
HAVE HER BACK.
I CONVINCED HER I WAS LIKE,
LOOK, I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU, WE
HAVE TO TAKE OUT MONICA AND
CHRISTINA.
I WILL VOTE YOUR WAY BUT I
SWEAR TO GOD...
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET
SCREWED.
IF YOU SCREW ME OVER...
YOU CAN COME TO ALABAMA AND
KILL ME.
I'VE BEEN GETTING RID OF THE
HEAD OF THE SNAKE THIS ENTIRE
GAME: MATT, BILL, NOW MONICA SO
I THINK IT'S PRETTY BRILLIANT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES!
Jeff: FIRST THING'S FIRST.
KAT, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, THREE
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL RACE
TO GET A BALL IN THE WATER.
YOU WILL THEN WORK TOGETHER TO
SHOOT THE BALL INTO A BASKET
WHILE THE MEMBERS OF THE OTHER
TRIBE TRY TO STOP YOU ANY WAY
THEY CAN.
EVERY TIME YOU GET A BALL IN THE
BASKET, YOU SCORE A POINT FOR
YOUR TRIBE.
FIRST TRIBE TO SCORE THREE WINS
IMMUNITY AND THE SAFE FROM
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT,
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FIRST ROUND IS THREE MEN TAKING
ON THREE MEN.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
GO, BOYS!
DEFENDING THE GOAL, TARZAN AND
MICHAEL.
COLTON MATCHES UP AGAINST JAY.
JONAS MATCHING UP AGAINST
TROYZAN.
HERE WE GO.
YOU GO WHEN IT HITS THE WATER.
GO.
JAY TAKES COLTON DOWN.
JAY TAKES JONAS DOWN.
JAY HAS IT OVER TO MICHAEL WHO'S
WIDE OPEN.
MICHAEL SCORES FOR SALANI!
SALANI LEADS 1-0.
WAY TO GO, JAY!
NEXT ROUND, TWO WOMEN; ONE MAN.
IT WILL BE SABRINA MATCHING UP
AGAINST CHRISTINA.
KAT MUCHING UP AGAINST MONICA.
GUARDING THE GOALS, MICHAEL AND
LEIF.
A LITTLE HEIGHT DISPARITY AT
THIS END.
SALANI LEADS 1-ZIP, HERE WE GO.
GO.
MICHAEL HIGH-STEPPING IT OUT TO
GET TO THAT BALL FIRST.
MICHAEL'S GOING TO GET THAT BALL
AND HAVE A FREE RUN BACK.
NOBODY MAY EVEN BE ABLE TO CATCH
HIM.
TOSSES OVER LEIF'S HEAD.
HE'S SO TALL.
MICHAEL MISSES FIRST TIME,
MISSES AGAIN.
LEIF'S TRYING TO GET ON HIM.
LEIF'S DOING A GOOD JOB.
LEIF MAKING IT TOUGH.
MIKE MISSES FOR THE FIFTH TIME.
MONICA HAS THE BALL.
LEIF TRYING TO PUSH MIKE AWAY.
NOT HAVING IT.
SABRINA AND MONICA GETTING INTO
IT.
KAT IN ON IT.
WHO'S GOING TO COME UP WITH THE
BALL.
LEIF HAS IT LEIF WITH A SHOT!
JUST MISSES.
COME ON, MIKE, QUICK!
THROW HIM OVER TO OUR SIDE.
Jeff: MIKE HAS IT TO
SALANI.
OVER TO SABRINA.
KAT WITH A FREE SHOT FOR SALANI.
SHE CAN'T GET IT TO GO.
LEIF THE SMALLEST GUY OUT THERE
BUT WORKING THE HARDEST.
TYING UP KAT.
MICHAEL TRYING TO STEAL THE
BALL, CHRISTINA GETS TOSSED AWAY
BY MIKE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
MIKE SCORES FOR SALANI.
SALANI LEADS 2-0.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HARD-FOUGHT POINT.
ALL RIGHT.
SALANI LEADS 2-ZIP.
WE'RE PLAYING TO THREE.
THIS COULD BE IT.
IT'S THREE WOMEN TAKING ON THREE
WOMEN IN WHAT COULD BE THE
DECIDING ROUND.
DEFENDING THE GOAL KAT AND
CHRISTINA.
MATCHUPS MONICA AND SABRINA.
AND ALICIA AND CHELSEA.
THIS IS IT.
MANONO NEEDS TO GET ON THE BOARD
HERE OR IT IS OVER.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
GET IT KAT!
IS.
Jeff: KAT RACING TO GET
THAT BALL FOR SALANI.
SHE'S GOT IT AND NOW RACING
BACK.
CHRISTINA GOT TO TAKE HER DOWN.
SHE DOES.
KAT PASSES OFF TO SABRINA.
ALICIA HOLDING CHELSEA BACK.
A LONG SHOT ALMOST GOES IN.
MONICA AND SABRINA GETTING INTO
IT NOW.
MONICA NOW FOR MANONO.
SHE'S GOT A FREE SHOT!
MONICA CAN SCORE AND SHE DOES!
MANONO'S ON THE BOARD.
SALANI LEADS 2-1.
YEAH!
NO SHUTOUTS!
LET'S GO MANONO!
LET'S GO!
Jeff: NEXT ROUND, THREE
MEN, SAME THREE THAT WENT IN THE
FIRST TIME.
MANONO GOING TO PUT COLTON DOWN
TO GUARD THE GOAL THIS TIME
AGAINST MICHAEL.
SALANI LEADS 2-1.
PLAYING TO THREE.
SALANI COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
COLTON SPRINTING THROUGH THE
WATER!
COLTON BEATS MICHAEL TO THE
BALL.
MICHAEL AND JAY NOW DOUBLE
TEAMING ON COLTON.
HELP ME!
Jeff: COLTON IS NOT GIVING
UP THAT BALL.
TARZAN TRYING TO TAKE JAY OFF OF
COLTON WHO WILL NOT GIVE UP THE
BALL.
JAY TAKES DOWN TROYZAN.
JONAS TAKING DOWN TROYZAN.
COLTON TAKES A LONG SHOT BUT
IT'S SHORT JAY GETS PASSED
TARZAN, JAY CAN WIN IT BUT HE'S
SHORT.
ANOTHER SHOT MISSES.
TROYZAN!
MISSES.
MICHAEL SCORES FOR SALANI.
SALANI WINS IMMUNITY!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT, GUYS!
GOOD JOB!
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
SALANI, CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
HEAD ON OUT.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
MANONO, SOMEBODY GOING HOME.
YOU HAVE TO AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
WE DID WHAT WE COULD.
IT'S KIND OF HARD GOING UP
AGAINST THAT KIND OF
COMPETITION.
AT LEAST IT WASN'T A SHUTOUT.
WE GOT ONE ON THE BOARD.
YUP.
ONE POINT.
PUT IT HERE, BABY.
GOOD JOB, MONICA.
I'M SORRY I LET YOU GUYS
DOWN.
YOU DID MORE THAN ANY OF US,
THOUGH.
WELL, NOW WHAT?
TODAY YOU WILL SEE AN OSCAR
PERFORMANCE FROM COLTON AND I
FOR THE BEST BLIND SIDE EVER
PLAYED.
MONICA'S GOING HOME TONIGHT.
SO IF YOU GUYS ARE VOTING OFF
A GIRL TONIGHT, PLEASE THINK
ABOUT STAYING STRONG.
DEFINITELY.
SO THAT WE CAN WIN THE
CHALLENGE TOMORROW.
I'M GLAD WE'RE ON THE SAME
PAGE.
AND I'M SURE SHE THINKS SHE'S IN
A SAFE SPOT BECAUSE SHE DID
SCORE US A BASKET BUT SHE'S
GOING HOME.
AND, HEY, ALICIA IS FOLLOWING ME
LIKE A FIDDLE.
IF FOLLOWING COLTON MEANS
VOTING OUT SOMEBODY ELSE AND
GETTING ME ONE STEP FURTHER TO
THE MILLION, AWESOME.
I COULD BE COLTON'S BITCH, I'LL
BE WHATEVER YOU WANT ME TO BE.
BUT JUST DON'T VOTE ME OFF.
(LAUGHS)
WE NEED TO WIN.
I KNOW.
SO MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST GET
RID OF TARZAN.
I THINK SO.
I DON'T WANT TO KEEP TALKING.
TELL MONICA THAT.
I WANTED TO SAY IT AND WHEN
ALICIA SAID IT IT WAS LIKE COOL,
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I WAS
THINKING AND TARZAN AT THE
CHALLENGE TODAY LOOKED LIKE WASH
AGO WOUNDED HIPPO TRYING TO WALK
OVER TO THE WATER SO I THINK IT
COMES TO A UNANIMOUS DECISION
THAT HE JUST NEEDS TO GO.
WE NEED TO GET RID OF TARZAN.
YEAH, THAT WAS A LITTLE
AWKWARD TODAY AT THE CHALLENGE.
ARE YOU OKAY WITH THAT?
I'M COOL WITH THAT.
.
THAT'S LITERALLY WHAT WE JUST
SAID.
LITERALLY.
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO WIN
TOMORROW.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
DON'T TELL TARZAN BUT WE'RE
GOING TO BLIND SIDE HIM.
OKAY.
JUST AS LONG AS IT'S NOT ME.
TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
WE HAVE... I MEAN, WE HAVE TO
WIN.
WE HAVE TO WIN.
NO DOUBT.
THAT'S THE THING.
THIS IS ONE WORLD, BABY, THIS
IS ONE WORLD.
WE HAVE TO THINK LIKE THAT.
ARE ARE YOU INN.
YEAH, IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES
TO KEEP US UNIFIED, WE'VE GOT TO
DO IT.
THE GUYS HAVE LOST SIGHT ON
THE NUMBERS GAME.
I MEAN, IT'S TARZAN TONIGHT.
IN MY MIND I'M THINKING THAT'S A
HUGE WIN FOR THE WOMEN THAT THE
MEN ARE ON BOARD TO TAKE OUT ONE
OF THE MEN.
WE'RE ALL THINKING THAT WE'VE
GOT TO GET RID OF TARZAN BECAUSE
HE'S KIND OF DIVIDING THE TRIBE
UP RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
AND SO...
TARZAN.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, FOR SURE.
TARZAN.
IN A WEIRD WAY, THAT WHOLE
EVENT THAT HAPPENED WITH LEIF
TELLING BILL THAT HE WAS GOING
HOME, THAT SORT OF TIPPED ME OFF
TO BEING A LITTLE LEERY OF LEIF
AND NOT TO TRUST HIM SO MUCH.
START BLOWING, SOMEBODY.
SO LEIF IS DEFINITELY A WILD
CARD AND HE DID DO SOME PRETTY
CRAZY THINGS AND WITH FOUR GUYS
AND THREE GIRLS.
ANYBODY COULD FLIP ON THE GUYS
SIDE AND JUST, YOU KNOW, MAKE IT
THE GIRLS GAME NOW.
THIS IS WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
WE'RE VOTING OUT MONICA.
SO IT'S MONICA?
NOW TELL ME WHO MONICA IS AGAIN?
PINK BIKINI.
YEAH.
OH, GOOD.
OKAY.
YEAH, YEAH.
SHE IS THE HEAD OF THE SNAKE,
DO YOU SEE WHAT I'M SAYING?
AND ALICIA SAID MONICA'S TRYING
TO PLAY ME, PLAY YOU, PLAY
EVERYBODY.
YEAH, SHE IS.
I'VE GOT ALICIA VOTING WITH
US JUST IN CASE YOU DON'T.
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
Y'ALL ARE ON BOARD?
YES, I AGREE YOU WITH YOU 100%.
PLEASE, LEIF.
I TOLD LEIF AND TARZAN BASICALLY
THIS IS THE DEAL.
WE'RE VOTING OUT MONICA BUT
TARZAN IS ALMOST LIKE HAVING A
GRANDFATHER WITH ALZHEIMER'S AND
YOU HAVE TO TELL HIM SOMETHING
87 TIMES.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP REPEATING IT,
REPEATING IT, REPEATING IT
BECAUSE HE FORGETS IT.
JUST REMEMBER, MONICA
TONIGHT.
RIGHT.
MONICA.
JUST REMEMBER MONICA LEWINSKY.
WAIT A MINUTE, WAIT A
MINUTE... OKAY.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE BEFORE WE
GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL HE KNOWS
WHO TO WRITE DOWN OR HE COULD
WRITE DOWN JENNY FOR ALL WE
KNOW.
DOES THIS LOOK OKAY?
YEAH, YOU LOOK GREAT.
IF I WERE WORKING WITH, LIKE,
SOMEWHAT INTELLIGENT PEOPLE WHO
COULD KIND OF HELP ME OUT AND I
DIDN'T HAVE TO MAKE ALL OF THE
DECISIONS IT WOULD BE SO EASY.
BUT LITERALLY IT'S REALLY HARD
BEING THE LEADER OF A BUNCH OF
IDIOTS.
IT'S SO DIFFICULT.
Jeff: SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
THIS NEW MANONO TRIBE.
JONAS, WHAT WAS YOUR REACTION OF
YOUR NEW TRIBE?
WELL, THE ODDS WERE NOT
STACKED IN OUR FAVOR, LET'S JUST
PUT IT THAT WAY.
Jeff: MONICA, GIVE ME YOUR
INPUT ON THIS NEW TRIBE.
WELL, BREAKING UP WAS HARD TO
DO.
WE'D GOTTEN CLOSE, THE GIRLS.
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY TURNED OUT TO
BE A BLESSING.
OUR BEACH IS BETTER, OUR FOOD IS
PLENTIFUL AND WE'VE... WE'RE
PLAYING LIKE A TEAM, I THINK.
Jeff: COLTON, DO YOU LIKE
MONICA'S POSITIVE ATTITUDE?
I MEAN, YEAH.
IF SHE THINKS THAT SHE CAN TURN
THIS SINKING SHIP AROUND, BY ALL
MEANS, HONEY, TAKE THE WHEEL.
WE NEED MONICA.
Jeff: ALICIA, IS IT
POSSIBLE THAT MONICA COULD BE
WHAT THIS TRIBE NEEDS TO HELP
TURN THINGS AROUND?
UM, I DEFINITELY THINK SHE'S
AN AWESOME PERSON, AMAZING
PERSON AND AMAZING SUPERMOM.
SHE'S VERY... VERY COMPETITIVE
AND VERY ATHLETIC.
THANK YOU.
AND SHE CAN KICK SOME ASS.
Jeff: I SMELL A "BUT"
COMING.
SHE CAN BE SEEN AS A THREAT.
THAT'S THE BUT.
THAT'S THE BUT?
BUT TO SAY I'M A THREAT, IT'S
MORE LIKE I'M TRYING TO HELP THE
TEAM INSTEAD OF TRYING TO GET
MYSELF FURTHER.
BUT I COULD SEE HOW YOU WOULD
PERCEIVE ME THAT WAY.
BUT SHE'S ONE OF THE MOST
HARDEST WORKING WOMEN I'VE EVER
SEEN.
WELL, GOOD.
THAT MAKES ME FEEL HAPPY.
Jeff: TARZAN, WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OF THIS NEW TRIBE?
WAS IT GOOD NEWS FOR YOU?
MY IMMEDIATE RESPONSE WAS TO
DROP MY ASSERTIVENESS TO A
DIFFERENT LOAD STAR, WHICH IS
ONE MEMBER OF THIS GROUP WHO
WOULD THEN LEAD THE FIRST FEW
DAYS OF THIS NEW TRIBE.
Jeff: SO THAT MEANS... HOLD
ON.
OKAY.
Jeff: I LOVE THIS.
IT'S KIND OF A GAME.
YOU DECIDED TO DROP YOUR
ASSERTIVENESS TO A DIFFERENT
LODE STAR WHICH IS ONE MEMBER OF
THIS GROUP.
YES.
Jeff: AND THAT WOULD BE...
I SHANT SAY BECAUSE THE GAME
IS AFOOT.
"I SHANT SAY"?
Jeff: SO YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO REVEAL BECAUSE WE HERE IN THE
MIDST OF THE GAME.
YES, SIR.
Jeff: LEIF, DO YOU
UNDERSTAND WHAT TARZAN SAYS?
HE'S GOT QUITE A VOCABULARY.
HE DEFINITELY IS A VERY
COMPLEX, VERY WISDOM KIND OF GUY
AND...
Jeff: IS IT HARD EVEN TO
TALK AROUND HIM?
DO YOU FIND YOURSELF SAYING "I
NEED BETTER WORDS THAN OKAY"?
YEAH, HE DEFINITELY HAS A LOT
OF BIG WORDS THAT I CAN KIND OF
COMPREHEND BUT HE ALSO HELPS
BETTER EXPLAINATE...
Jeff: SEE, BETTER
EXPLAINATE, NOT A WORD.
AND WHAT HE SAID IS A NEO-LOW
JIM.
Jeff: WHICH IS WHAT?
MAKING UP THE WORD THAT
SOUNDS SIMILAR TO THE WORD YOU
MEAN TO SAY.
Jeff: AWESOME.
IT'S IMPRESSIVE, YOUR
VOCABULARY.
NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE THAT.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: BUT THE NEED TO SHARE
IT AND THE NEED TO BE HEARD CAN
BE DISRUPTIVE.
DO YOU EVER SENSE THAT?
WELL, IN MY OWN ENVIRONMENT
IT'S A THING WE DO.
WE TRY TO BE VERY, VERY PRECISE.
Jeff: WHAT IS YOUR WORLD?
WHAT HAVE YOUR SHARED WITH YOUR
GROUP ABOUT YOUR WORLD?
THE GAME IS AFOOT, JEFF.
Jeff: SO THAT REMAINS A
MYSTERY?
YEAH.
Jeff: I KNOW YOU HAVE 14
PETS.
I HAVE 14 PETS.
I'M A MEDIC.
A WIFE NAMED TERRY.
I COLLECT BUGS.
HE HAS APHAGIA.
YES.
Jeff: I NEED A DICTIONARY.
I HAVE A NOMINAL APHAGIA.
IT'S A SPECIFIC APHAGIA FOR
PEOPLE'S NAMES THAT I HAVE HAD
ALL MY LIFE.
I CAN'T REMEMBER A PERSON'S
NAME.
IT'S CALLED NOMINAL APHAGIA.
Jeff: DO YOU KNOW THE NAMES
OF YOUR TRIBE MEMBERS?
I.
I... DO?
(LAUGHS).
Jeff: LET'S SEE.
OKAY, TARZAN.
(LAUGHS)
ALICIA, LEIF, COLTON, GOSH, CAN
YOU BELIEVE IT?
UM...... MONICA.
CHRISTINA... UM... DON'T SAY IT!
STARTS WITH A "J."
JONAS.
THAT'S IT.
Jeff: TARZAN, JUST SO I'M
CLEAR, YOU WEREN'T PUTTING ME
ON, YOU WERE STRUGGLING.
YEAH.
Jeff: AND HAD MONICA NOT
GIVEN YOU THE FIRST LETTER, WE
MIGHT STILL BE HERE.
POSSIBLY, IF YOU WAITED THAT
LONG.
(LAUGHS).
Jeff: WELL, AFTER 14 DAYS,
SOMEBODY IS ABOUT TO BE VOTED
OUT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JONAS, YOU'RE UP.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, TARZAN.
TWO VOTES TARZAN.
MONICA.
TWO VOTES TARZAN; ONE VOTE
TWO VOTES TARZAN; TWO VOTES
MONICA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES MONICA, TWO
VOTES TARZAN.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: ONE WORLD."
MONICA.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH.
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
WOW.
WHAT THE?
MONICA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, YOU ADMIT THE OTHER TRIBE
IS STRONGER AND THEN YOU VOTE
OUT ARGUABLY YOUR STRONGEST
MEMBER BECAUSE SHE WAS TOO BIG
OF A THREAT.
INTERESTING STRATEGY ON ONLY DAY
14.
SEE HOW IT PLAYS OUT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
RUN!
Jeff: COLTON'S RAGE TAKES
AIM.
YOU CAN QUIT OR JUMP IN THAT
FIRE, WHICH EVER IS MORE
CONVENIENT FOR YOU.
Jeff: AND THE GAME CLAIMS
ANOTHER VICTIM.
HEART RATE IS UP TO 120.
I AM FREAKING OUT.
THIS IS WORSE THAN WHAT I REALLY
THOUGHT IT WAS.
Jeff: LET'S BRING IT IN.
I'M EXTREMELY DISAPPOINTED.
I CAME HERE TO WIN.
I CHASED MY HUSBAND ALL OVER
STADIUMS FOR 11 YEARS OF
FOOTBALL AND ALL I WAS LOOKING
FORWARD TO WAS HIM COMING TO THE
"SURVIVOR" STADIUM.
THE DUMBEST THING THAT I COULD
HAVE DONE WAS TRUST COLTON.
I GUESS I BLAME MYSELF FOR BEING
OUTWITTED