>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"."
>> THIS IS MY FINAL FOUR.
>> Jeff: THERE WAS A MAJORITY
OF ALLIANCE MADE UP OF MALCOLM,
DENISE, SKUPIN AND LISA.
>> IF IT'S WORKED IT WILL BE THE
BEST THING THAT'S HAPPENED TO ME
IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: CRACKS STARTED TO
FORM.
>> WE CAN TAKE MALCOLM OUT AND
THE IDOL.
>> MALCOLM IS PLAYING A
BRILLIANT GAME.
I WANT TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN ON
WIN.
>> ABY CAME UP WITH A PLAN TO
SAVE HERSELF.
>> I WILL HAVE TO PLAY MY HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> Jeff: ATTEMPTING TO TRICK
EVERYONE INTO THINKING SHE HAD A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> IF YOU TELL A LIE LONG
ENOUGH.
EVERYBODY STARTS TO BELIEVE IT.
>> Jeff: IT WASN'T HER PLAN
THAT SAVED HER.
>> RIGHT NOW YOU'RE TELLING ME A
MILLION DOLLARS IS MORE
IMPORTANT THAN MY WORD.
DON'T BE HYPOCRITICAL.
>> NOBODY CAN STAND HAVING HER
AROUND.
SHE'S A BITCH.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
LISA MADE IT CLEAR WHO SHE
WANTED TO SIT TO AT THE END.
IF I HAD TO CHOOSE SOMEBODY WHO
DESERVES TO BE THERE OR I COULD
SIT NEXT TO SOMEBODY I THINK I
COULD BEAT--
>> I THINK I WOULD SILT NEXT TO
SOMEBODY I COULD BEAT.
>> Jeff: THE SIXTH MEMBER OF
OUR JURY, CARTER.
FIVE ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
>> WOW, 34, GUYS.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, GUYS.
>> HEY, FINAL FIVE.
>> FINAL FIVE IS HUGE.
>> THANKS FOR KEEPING ME, GUYS.
I SHOULD THINK BECAUSE--
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW
TO THANK YOU GUYS.
I MEAN-- I SURVIVED ANOTHER
TRIBAL.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS.
I AM OVER THE MOON.
THANK YOU AGAIN.
I MEAN, I-- I'M IN AWE, REALLY.
IT'S GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> ANOTHER COUPLE OF DAYS FOR US
ALL, RIGHT.
>> HEY, ONE DAY AT A TIME.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> I BLUFFED WITH MY FANTASY HID
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AND I
DON'T EVEN THEY BUY IT OR NOT,
BUT I'M GOING TO TRY TO PULL IT
OFF AT NEXT TRIBAL AGAIN AND SEE
HOW IT GOES.
>> THAT WAS A HARD ONE.
>> THAT WAS A VERY HARD ONE.
>> WHAT A GOOD YOUNG MAN.
>> YEAH, HE TOOK IT REALLY
PERSONALLY.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS HARD.
CARTER IS JUST ONE OF THE NICEST
GUYS YOU'D EVER WANT TO MEET.
>> THAT'S THE PART THAT YOU--
THE PART THAT HEEL GROW UP FROM,
YOU KNOW, FROM THIS EXPERIENCE,
I HOPE.
>> IT REALLY DOESN'T SEEM FAIR.
I MEAN, THIS GAME ISN'T FAIR.
BUT IF I HAD A CHOICE TO BRING
SOMEBODY THAT WAS WORTHY OF
BEING THERE OR SOMEBODY I COULD
BEAT, I WOULD BRING SOMEBODY I
COULD BEAT.
>> FINAL FIVE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S WEIRD IS I
WAS THINKING ABOUT YOU, ABI, AND
I THINK YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONAB HERE BUT I THINK YOU
THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA BE HERE
WITH VERY DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
>> OH.
( LAUGHS )
IT'S.
>> IT'S JUST IRONIC, YOU KNOW.
>> IRONIC.
THAT'S A GOOD WORD.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT,
LISA SAID SHE WANTS TO GO TO THE
END WITH SOMEBODY SHE THINKS SHE
CAN BEAT.
IT WAS REALLY AN EYE OPENER THAT
SHE'S THINKING THAT
STRATEGICALLY.
SO GOOD ON HER, BUT NOW I KNOW
EXACTLY WHO SHE IS LOOKING FOR
TO TAKE TO THE FINAL THREE.
HER HEAD IS IN THE GAME.
SHE TIPPED IT OFF AND IT MAKES
HER INTRUS GOING FORWARD.
DOING A LOT BETTER.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA GO GET SOME
WATER.
>> SHE ANNOUNCES WITH TRUMPETS
THAT "I'M GOING INTO THE WOOD
FOR A WHILE."
>> ABI'S COME UP WITH THIS COCK
AND BULL STORY ABOUT HAVING AN
IDOL FOR A FEW VOTES NOW.
>> INTERESTING, "THANK YOU FOR
KEEPING ME AROUND."
VERY HUMBLE.
>> SHE'S KEEPING THE ACT GOING
AROUND CAMP THAT HE STILL HAS
ONE, BUT THE THREAT WAS SO HIGH
ON HER LAST NIGHT TO GO HOME AND
SHE WAS SO RELIEVED THAT SHE
DIDN'T, THERE'S NO WAY SHE WOULD
HAVE HELD ON TO IT LAST NIGHT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
IF SHE WOULD HAVE THAT
SURPRISED, SHE WOULD HAVE PLAYED
IT.
>> MALCOLM IS NOT GOING ANYWHERE
ANY TIME SOON.
HE IS DRL USING HIS HIDDEN
IMMUNITY THIS TIME AROUND.
I NEED TO MAKE SURE THE ALLIANCE
THAT DEFELICE AND MALCOLM HAVE
IS DESTROYED BECAUSE THEY ARE
VERY DANGEROUS TOGETHER.
AND IF DENISE DOES NOT WIN THE
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, SHE
NEEDS TO GO HOME ASAP.
>> YEAH, THOSE TWO.
>> LISA, BE VERY CAREFUL.
DENISE, SKUPIN AND MALCOLM ARE
SO IN AN ALLIANCE WITH EACH
OTHER, AND YOU'RE SO ON THE
BOTTOM.
>> REALLY?
WHAT DID THEY SAY?
>> LISA, SHE KNOWS SHE CAN BEAT
YOU.
AND SHE KNOWS THAT SHE-- AND YOU
KNOW, MALCOLM AND SKUPIN ARE ALL
AT THE SAME LEVEL.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THIS ALLIANCE OF FOUR,
YOU ARE TOTALLY ON THE BOTTOM.
I WOULD BE VERY CAREFUL.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE ABI FOR A
SECOND, BUT I NEED ABI CLOSE
WHETHER WE KEEP HER OR SHES ANY
TO THSHES ANYJURY.
IF WE KEEP HER I NEED HER CLOSE
TO TAKE TO THE END AND THAT
FIELD REALLY JUKED IN, BUT I'M
NOT GOING TO LIE.
THAT IS THE RELATIONSHIP I HAVE
WITH ABI.
IT'S ONE TO USE HER FOR MY BEST
GAME PLAN.
>> I KNOW THAT IF I'M VOTED OUT
FIVE, YOU'RE FOUR FOR SURE.
FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN, FROM
EVERYTHING THAT'S GOING ON.
>> OKAY, I APPRECIATE THAT.
THANK YOU FOR THE HEADS-UP ON
THAT.
RIGHT NOW, IT APPEARS I HAVE
OPTIONS FROM WHICH TO CHOOSE.
I WOULD LOVE TO BE ABLE TO VOTE
OFF DENISE AND KEEP ABI AROUND.
THEN AGAIN, I MAY NEED TO VOTE
OFF ABI IN ORDER TO KEEP THE
FOUR ALLIANCE STRONG.
SO I HAVE ALL THESE GREAT, YOU
KNOW, SCENARIOS IN MY HEAD BUT I
DO BELIEVE I'M TAKING CONTROL OF
MY DESTINY, BUT PART OF TAKING
CONTROL OF MY DESTINY IS WAITING
TO THE RIGHT TIME TO MAKE MY BIG
MOVE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU WILL RACE UP AND
OVER A SLIDE AND INTO THE OCEAN
WHERE YOU WILL GRAB A BUNDLE OF
RINGS AND RACE BACK.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED BOTH
BUNDLES YOU MUST LAND ONE RING
ON EACH OF THE FIVE PEGS.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER WILL BE
PICKED UP IN A HELICOPTER.
YOU WILL THEN LAND AND BOARD A
BOAT WHERE WE HAVE PIZZA AND
SOFT DRINKS WAITING FOR YOU.
TO DO SOME WHALE SHARK WATCHING.
>> WHOA!
>> Jeff: IN ADDITION THE
WINNER WILL CHOOSE TWO PEOPLE TO
JOIN THEM ON THIS REWARD, HUGE
OPPORTUNITY TO MAKE A STRATEGIC
MOVE IN THIS GAME.
I KNOW IT'S WORTH PLAYING FOR.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOT, AND WE'LL
GET STARTED
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
SKUPIN OVER FIRST.
THERE GOES MALCOLM.
NICE BIG HIT.
LISA FLYING DOWN
EVERYBODY OFF TO A QUICK START.
YOU'RE UNTYING RINGS.
ONCE YOU HAVE A BUNDLE OF RINGS,
HEAD BACK.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT AGAIN.
SKUPIN FIRST HEADING BACK.
MALCOLM RIGHT BEHIND.
HERE COMES DENISE.
ABI GETTING BACK.
LISA STRUGGLING.
SKUPIN IS BACK AND HEADING OVER
AGAIN.
MALCOLM IS BACK.
HE'S HEADING OVER AGAIN!
HERE COMES DENISE.
SHE'S GOING FOR HER SECOND RIDE.
LISA WORKING HER WAY THROUGH
THAT SAND.
SKUPIN, HE'S GOT HIS SECOND AND
FINAL BUNDLE OF RINGS.
MALCOLM HEADING BACK WITH HIS
SECOND RINGS.
LISA NOT GIVING UP.
DENISE NOW HEADING BACK WITH HER
SECOND BUNDLE OF RINGS.
ABI WORKING ON HER SECOND
BUNDLE.
LISA NOW IN THE WATER LOOKING
FOR HER SECOND BUNDLE.
ONCE YOU'RE BACK, START TOSSING
YOUR RINGS.
SKUPIN LAND A RING.
MALCOLM LAND HIS FIRST RING.
SKUPIN LAND A SECOND RING.
SKUPIN LANDS HIS THIRD RING.
SKUPIN HAS DOMINATED THIS
CHALLENGE FROM THE BEGINNING,
AND HE'S NOT SLOWING DOWN.
SKUPIN WITH THREE RINGS.
MALCOLM WITH ONE.
LISA NOW BACK TO JOIN IN ON
THIS.
IT'S STILL ANYBODY'S CHALLENGE.
OH, MALCOLM, CLOSE.
MALCOLM SCORES HIS SECOND RING.
COUPIN SCORES HIS FOURTH RING.
SKUPIN DOWN TO ONE LAST RING.
JUST MISSING!
LISA SCORES A RING.
DENISE SCORES A RING.
MALCOLM WITH HIS THIRD RING.
MALCOLM WITH HIS FOURTH RING.
ONE LEFT.
SKUPIN JUST NISSES WITH HIS
FIFTH AND FINAL RING.
IT IS NOW DOWN TO SKUPIN AND
MALCOLM.
MALCOLM MISSES.
SKUPIN SCORES HIS FIFTH RING!
SKUPIN WINS REWARD!
( APPLAUSE )
>> GOOD JOB, SKUPIN.
>> GOOD JOB, SCOOP.
>> GOOD JOB, BABE.
GIVE ME A HUG.
GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: SCIEWFIN, COME ON
OVER.
>> LET'S GO.
>>
( APPLAUSE )
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: YOU WON A REWARD.
A CHOPPER IS GOING TO COME IN
AND PICK YOU UP.
>> REMEMBER MY LAST CHOPPER
RIDE?
>> Jeff: YOUR LAST CHOPPER
RIDE YOU WERE BEING EVACUATED.
>> YOU PUT ME ON IT AND YOU PUT
ME ON IT AGAIN.
>> Jeff: A BETTER AFTERNOON IN
STORE FOR YOU THAN THE LAST TIME
YOU RODE A CHOPPER.
YOU'LL GET ON A BOAT, PITA, SOFT
DRINKS.
YOU NEED TWO PEOPLE TO JOIN YOU.
WHO IS GOING TO GO WITH YOU?
>> JEFF, BIGGER THAN THIS GAME,
MALCOLM GAVE MY BOY SOMETHING
THAT WILL LAST ME A LIFETIME,
WAY LONGER THAN PIZZA WILL, AND
I'M GETTING CHOCKED UP EVEN
TALKING ABOUT IT, BUT I GOTTA
TAKE MALCOLM.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, COME ON
OVER.
>> THANK YOU, MIKE.
>> Jeff: GOOD DEED ARE STIEMED
REWARDED IN THIS GAME.
NOT OFTEN.
YOU HAVE ONE OTHER CHOICE.
THREE WOMEN SITTING OVER THERE.
LISA, COME ON OVER GIRL.
>> YA!
>> I GOTTA TAKE YOU.
AND, DENISE, ALL MY FOOD IS
YOURS.
>> AND LEAVE THE DISHES.
I'LL DO THOSE WHEN I GET BACK.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN HAS MADE HIS
DECISION.
ABI, DENISE, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> Jeff: ABI, YOU LOOK
HEARTBROKEN.
>> I AM.
I GUESS MY VOTE DOESN'T MEAN
ANYTHING
>> ENJOY IT.
TAKE IT IN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
CHOPPER IS COMING IN.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD DOWN THE BEACH.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
>> A MACHETE.
KILL THEM WHEN THEY'RE BACK.
>> I WAS VERY CRUSHED WHEN I
WASN'T PICKED TO GO ON THIS
REWARD.
IT JUST PROVES TO ME THAT, ONCE
AGAIN, I AM ON THE BOTTOM OF
WHATEVER ALLIANCE.
>> WE'LL MAKE THE BEST OF IT,
RIGHT?
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE, I
GOTTA GO HOME WITH DENISE.
DENISE IS, LIKE, A HORRIBLE
PERSON.
SO IT'S NOT A FUN DAY.
I WAS REALLY HEARTBROKEN,
REALLY.
>> OH.
IT'S GOING TO BE A PAINFUL
AFTERNOON.
IT'S LIKE THE FIRST DATE WITH
THE KID WHO, LIKE, PULLED YOUR
HAIR ALL TIME IN KINDERGARTEN,
OR SPIT IN YOUR LUNCH, AND ALL
OF A SUDDEN YOU'RE ON A DATE.
AND IT'S LIKE, WOW, OKAY.
SO I'M JUST GOING TO MAKE NICE.
OH, ABI, I SORRY, I KNOW YOU
WANTED TO GO.
>> I WANTED TO GO SO BADLY.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, I AM LITERALLY
THE SWING VOTE HERE, AND I DON'T
THINK THAT MICHAEL SEES IT.
IT'S KIND OF WEIRD.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE I JUST WANT TO GET TO
THE END OF THE DAY, SO I'M GOING
TO LET HER STRATEGIZE.
I'M GOING TO LET HER TALK ABOUT
HOW SHE'S THE SWING VOTE.
>> YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN AT IMMUNITY, YOU KNOW.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHO'S GOING TO
WIN.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> NEXT TRIBAL IS MY LAST CHANCE
TO PLAY MY IDOL.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
SHE KEEPS TALKING ABOUT HAVING A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
NONE OF US BELIEVES SHE HAS ONE,
NOT FOR A MINUTE.
IT'S JUST ABOUT GETTING THROUGH
THE AFTERNOON AND MAKING IT AS
TOLERABLE AS CAN BE.
>> ANYWAY, FOOD FOR THOUGHT.
>> FOOD FOR THOUGHT, FOR SURE.
I WANT TO HANG MYSELF, GOUGE MY
EYES OUT.
IF I COULD HAVE NEEDLES THAT GO
RIGHT INTO MY EARDRUMS I WOULD
BE GOOD FOR THE AFTERNOON.
>> I'M GOING BACK AND FORTH
BETWEEN THE CHOCOLATE AND THE
WHITE CHOCOLATE.
>> I'M GOING PIZZA, WHITE
CHOCOLATE.
PIZZA AT THE VERY TOP.
AFTER A SHORT LITTLE RIDE, WE
END UP ON THIS BOAT AND THERE'S
THIS GREAT SPREAD OF WHAT A
COUPLE OF US HAVE BEEN CRAVING
FOR A LONG TIME, WHICH IS PIZZA.
AND THEN THEY HAVE SOFT DRINKS
AND COOKIES, WHICH I HAVE
ALREADY SHOWN A WEAKNESS FOR OUT
HERE.
>> I'M DRINKING POP.
I HAVEN'T HAD POP IN 30 YEARS.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> I'VE BEEN ALIVE FOR 24 YEARS,
NEVER ONCE SAID THE WORDS, "I'M
DRINKING POP."
MICHAEL SKUPIN DOESN'T EAT SUGAR
IN REAL LIFE AND HE OVER-ATE ON
SUGAR AND ACTED LIKE A DRUNK
CHICK AT A BAR.
HE'S LAUGHING AND ROLLING AROUND
IN HIS SEAT.
HE'S TRYING ON CLOTHES.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, MICHAEL SKUPIN
IS FUN TO BE AROUND.
WHO KNEW HE HAD THAT SIDE OF
HIM?
>> I'M LOOKING FOR SHADOWS THE
SIZE OF MY STOMACH.
>STOMACH.
WOW I HAVEN'T HAD A SODA IN 30
YEARS.
AND I HAD THREE OR FOUR OF
THEM-- I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE GOOD.
>> WE IS THIS WHOLE TEAM OF
LOCAL FISHERMEN TRYING TO FIND
ONE OF THESE FISH.
THEY FINALLY SPOT A SHADOW IN
THE WATER.
THEN IT TURNS OUT WE'RE NOT EVEN
LOOKING OVER THE BOAT AT THESE
GUYS.
HE HANDS A FLIPPER AND MASK.
YOU'RE GOING TO PUT ME IN THE
WATER WITH THE WORLD'S BIGGEST
FISH?
MY HANDS STARTED SHAKING.
>> OKAY, GO!
>> WE DOVE IN LIKE NAVY SEALs,
AND THE GUIDE GRABBED MY HAND,
AND HE POINTS.
AND THEN OUT OF THE BLUE, I MEAN
LITERALLY, POOF.
THIS HUMONGOUS WHALE SHARK
APPEARED.
AND IT'S SO BIG IT NEVER ENDS.
IT JUST KEEPS SWIMMING AND KEEPS
SWIMMING, KEEPS SWIMMING.
>> TO SEE SOMETHING THAT HUGE
AND TO BE AROUND SOMETHING THAT
POWERFUL WAS AWE-INSPIRING.
THAT FISH WAS JUST MASSIVE.
>> I'M SWIMMING WITH THIS THING
WITH THE DORSAL FIN THAT LOOK
LIKE A SHARK, AND IT'S SO
INTIMIDATING BECAUSE YOU THINK
AT ANY SECOND IT COULD JUST TURN
ON YOU AND BITE YOU, EAT YOU
>> OH, MY GOD!
A WHALE SHARK HEAD BUTTED
MICHAEL SKUPIN.
FUNNIEST THING I'VE SEEN IN MY
LIFE.
AND MY MIND WHAT BECOME SO
CALCULATING AFTER A MONTH AND A
HALF IN THIS GAME, I'M THINKING,
"OH, GREAT, ONE LESS
COMPETITOR."
>> YOU GUYS DIDN'T WARN ME.
I RAN RIGHT INTO IT.
>> YOU WERE DOWN THERE SHOW
BOATING.
WHAT I WAS SUPPOSED TO DO?
IN THE MIDST OF ALL THIS
EXCITEMENT, I HAVE A GAME TO
PLAY.
I'VE BEEN THE DRIVING OF THE
LAST TWO VOTES AND I NEED TO
CONTINUE TO BE THAT.
ME, YOU, AND 69 ARE IN THE SAME
BOAT.
THE ONLY WAY ANY OF US HAS A
SHOT OF WINNING IS IF DENISE
ISN'T SITTING THERE.
THAT'S THE SITUATION WE'RE STUCK
WITH.
NOBODY BEATS DENISE, THE WOMAN--
>> EVERY TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NOBODY WORKS HARDER, AND SHE
HASN'T BETRAYED ANYBODY.
IT'S A BLOW-OUT IF SHE GOES.
BUT IF WE DO THIS, THERE'S NO
RISK AT ALL THE ENTIRE WAY
THROUGH UNTIL THE FINAL THREE.
MYSELF AND DENISE HAVE BEEN
TIGHT SINCE DAY ONE, BUT IN MY
MIND, MY BEST CHANCE TO GET TO
THE FINAL THREE AND TO WIN A
FINAL THREE IS GOING TO BE NEXT
TO LISA AND SKUPIN.
SO I NEED TO MAKE THEM GIVE ME
THEIR WORD ON A FINAL THREE DEAL
THAT CUTS DENISE OUT.
>> FROM MY PERSPECTIVE, YOU'VE
NEVER LIED TO ME, YOU'VE NEVER
LIED TO ME.
I'VE NEVER LIED TO HIM.
I LIKE CEMENTING THE DEAL.
HAVING SOMETHING THAT'S DONE
IS-- YOU KNOW, YOU END UP LIKE
PENNER-- LET ME THINK ABOUT, LET
ME THINK ABOUT IT, LET ME THINK
ABOUT IT AND YOU COME BACK AND
IT'S TOO LATE, LARPY.
MALCOLM AT THIS POINT WOULD BE
THE BEST PERSON TO FORM AN
ALLIANCE WITH FOR THE FINAL
THREE BECAUSE HE'S THE MOST
DANGEROUS TO WIN AN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
SO IF HE WINS, HE HAS MORE POWER
IN WHO GETS TO COME TO THE FINAL
THREE.
>> I HAVE LOVED NOT HAVING THE
STRESS.
ONCE WE MADE A DECISION WITH THE
FINAL FOUR, NOT HAVING TO WORRY
OR SCRAMBLE OR STRESS.
SO, I MEAN, I LIKE THIS.
I LIKE THIS IDEA A LOT.
>> SHOULD WE DO IT?
>> I THINK SO.
>> SO YOU GUYS HAVE MY WORD.
>> ALL THE THINGSES I PROMISED
BEFORE.
>> THIS IS MY FINAL THREE.
>> THIS IS IT, FINAL THREE,
BABY!
>> WHOOO!
>> SKUPIN'S REALLY ON BOARD WITH
THIS, AND I DON'T HAVE A CHANCE
TO TRY TO TALK SOME SENSE INTO
HIM, SO I CAN SAY, YEAH, LOVE
IT, MAKES ALL THE SENSE IN THE
WORLD TO ME, US THREE TO THE
END.
AND IF IT'S THE BEST WAY FOR ME
TO GO, GREAT.
I'VE MADE A DEAL.
AND IF IT'S NOT, THEN I CAN MAKE
ANOTHER DEAL.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> WHAT A GREAT DAY!
>> WHEN I GOT UP IT WAS LIKE
WHAT WAS THAT.
IT WAS LIKE, ON FIRE.
LIKE-- WHOOO!
WHATEVER IT IS, IT'S DOING
SOMETHING.
BECAUSE THIS IS NOT JUST
SLEEPING WRONG ON-- IT'S--
AGAIN, IT STARTED SHARP BURNING,
LIKE INSTANT, JUST, LIKE,
BURNING.
>> JUST STAY CALM.
JUST BREATHE.
>> I JUST HAVE TO--
>> JUST BREATHE THROUGH IT.
>> THIS MORNING I GOT UP AND AS
SOON AS I MOVED, IT JUST--
THERE'S SHARP INCREDIBLE
STINGING.
IT WAS LIKE MY NECK, MY WHOLE
NECK WAS ON FIRE RIGHT HERE.
IT'S JUST ACHE AND PAIN.
LIKE, JUST-- LIKE THIS HURTS TO
JUST EVEN LIFT MY ARM AND TO
MOVE MY NECK
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M HAVING AN
ALLERGIC REACTION TO SOMETHING
THAT BIT ME.
>> THAT COULD BE A POISON.
>> I'VE GOT, LIKE, FANG MARKS
SOMEWHERE IN MY NECK.
CLEARLY IT WASN'T A MOSQUITO.
AH!
I'M TRYING TO TELL MYSELF TO
SUCK IT UP.
YOU HAVE THREE DAYS LEFT.
LIKE, SERIOUSLY.
IF IT'S JUST AN ALLERGIC
REACTION THAT WILL PASS, THEN
WE'RE GOOD.
BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT IT
IS.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WAS A SPIDER.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN A LITTLE
LIZARD.
THERE ARE TARANTULAS OUT HERE.
WE'VE SEEN SCORPIONS.
WE'VE SEEN A SNAKE GOING UP THE
TREE.
YOU FORGET THAT, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S STUFF EVERYWHERE OUT
HERE.
SO I'M JUST HOPING IT PASSES.
IT'S NOT GOING TO KILL ME.
BUT IT'S REALLY, REALLY PAINFUL
RIGHT NOW.
>> JUST PUSH OUT WHATEVER POISON
IS IN THERE.
JUST MAKE IT GO THROUGH SO FAST.
IT WILL BE COMPLETELY GONE.
FEEL YOUR ARMS AROUND HER JUST
ROCKING HER LIKE A BABY, LIKE A
MOTHER WOULD, BLOW ON HER WOUND.
YOU CREATED OUR BODIES AND YOU
KNOW WHAT TO DO, SO WE'RE ASKING
YOU TO RELIEVE THIS PAIN AND
HEAL THIS AND MAKE THIS GO AWAY
AND COMFORT HER IN THE MEANTIME.
>> LORD, WE HAVE A CHALLENGE.
WE HAVE A BIG DAY.
WE JUST ASK YOU, LORD, LET
DENISE FINISH THIS GAME.
>> I FEEL REALLY BAD THAT DENISE
IS HURT, BUT WHEN YOU HAVE AN
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE COMING UP AND
IT'S FINAL FOUR, I'M LIKE KIND
OF RELIEVED A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT SCARES ME THE MOST IS
FREAKING DENISE WINNING
IMMUNITY.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
OH!
>> THE REALITY OF THINGS ARE I
CAME HERE NOT TO BE FEELING BAD
FOR OTHER PEOPLE.
I CAME HERE TO WIN A MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
SO HOW IS EVERYBODY HOLDING UP
AFTER 36 DAYS OUT HERE?
>> UNFORTUNATELY IT HAS NOT BEEN
A GREAT MORNING IN THE
PHILIPPINES.
>> Jeff: WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I GOT BIT THIS MORNING, SO
STILL FEELING QUITE A BIT OF THE
EFFECTS OF THAT.
SO, YEAH, IT'S BEEN A LITTLE
MISERABLE.
>> Jeff: ABI, FOR YOU,
POSSIBLE OPENING.
>> POSSIBLE.
POSSIBILITY.
YEAH.
IS THERE COMPLICATED GAME, ISN'T
IT?
ONE PERSON GETS INJURED, AND
WHILE YOU HAVE EMPATHY FOR THAT
INJURY, THERE'S ANOTHER PART
THAT SAYS GIVES ME A BETTER SHOT
AT WINNING.
>> THAT'S BEEN MY LIFE, GOING
AFTER OPPORTUNITY.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
MALCOLM, GIVE IT UP.
>> YOU COME AND GET IT.
>> Jeff: NOBODY HAS GIVEN ME
THIS NECKLACE.
I'VE HAD TO TAKE IT OFF EVERY
TIME.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
USE PLANKS TO CROSS A ROPE
BRIDGE COLLECTING PIECED TO A
MAZE.
ONCE YOU ARE ACROSS, YOU WILL
ASSEMBLE A MAZE AND USE A BALL
TO COMPLETE IT.
THE FIRST PERSON TO FINISH IT
WINS EMIMMUNITY.
GUARANTEED A ONE-IN-FOUR SHOT AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE AFTER 36 VERY TOUGH DAYS
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FOUR, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
RIGHT OUT OF THE GATE, DIFFERENT
STRATEGIES.
GRABBING PIECES TO THE MAZE
ALONG THE WAY, SKUPIN HAS HIS
FIRST PIECE.
DENISE HAS HER FIRST PIECE.
MALCOLM HAS ONE.
LISA HAS ONE.
ABI STILL WORKING ON HER FIRST
PIECE.
IF YOU FALL OFF, YOU'VE GOT TO
COME BACK.
DENISE, EVEN WITH AN INJURY,
LOOKS TO BE MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS VERY QUICKLY.
ABI HAS HER FIRST PIECE.
EVERYBODY IN THIS.
MALCOLM HAS HIS SECOND PIECE.
SKUPIN HAS BOTH PIECES.
LISA HAS BOTH PIECES.
DENISE HAS BOTH PIECES.
MALCOLM RIGHT THERE WITH SKUPIN
IN THE LEAD.
MALCOLM FALLS OFF.
A HUGE SETBACK FOR MALCOLM.
HE WAS RIGHT THERE AT THE END.
NOW HAS TO GO BACK TO THE START
SKUPIN IS THE FIRST TO CROSS.
HE CAN START ASSEMBLING HIS
MAZE.
DENISE IS ACROSS.
SHE CAN START HER MAZE.
LISA'S ACROSS.
MALCOLM LOST A LOT OF TIME IN
ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES IN THIS
GAME.
ABI'S ACROSS.
SHE CAN START WORKING ON THE
MAZE.
THIS MAZE ONLY GOES TOGETHER ONE
WAY.
AND YOU WILL KNOW BECAUSE THE
BALL WILL FIT THROUGH IT.
IF YOU FIND A ROADBLOCK, IT'S
NOT RIGHT.
IF THE PIECES AREN'T LINING UP,
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
MALCOLM DEAD LAST HAS TO REDO
THE ENTIRE COURSE.
>> WHERE IS THAT PIECE?
>> Jeff: DENISE LOOKS TO BE
MAKING A LOT OF PROGRESS
QUICKLY.
IF YOU WIN THIS CHALLENGE, YOU
ARE GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FOUR
YOU LOSE, YOU COULD BE GOING
HOME.
A LOT OF PIECES WILL LINE UP,
BUT ALL OF THEM NEED.
HARD TO TELL IF YOU'RE RIGHT
UNTIL YOU'RE FINISHED.
>> HOW CAN THAT NOT FIT?
>> Jeff: MALCOLM IS ACROSS
NOW.
HE'S GOING TO GET BACK IN THIS.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THE MAZE.
MALCOLM, YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE UP
SOME TIME.
DENISE GETTING CLOSE.
LISA TRYING TO FIGURE THIS
PUZZLE OUT.
ABI AND SKUPIN FALL A LITTLE
BEHIND.
>> THAT CAN'T BE, THAT CAN'T BE.
>> Jeff: DENISE THINKS SHE HAS
IT
>> UGH, THAT'S NOT IT.
>> Jeff: DENISE LOOKS VERY
CLOSE BUT SOMETHING IS NOT
RIGHT.
ONE PIECE CAN JAM YOU UP.
ONE PIECE COULD COST YOU A
MILLION BUCKS.
HUGE STAKES.
LISA, SKUPIN, ABI, FALLING OUT
OF IT!
NOTHING EASY ABOUT THIS
CHALLENGE!
MALCOLM, WHO FELL OUT OF THIS
EARLY MAKING A LOT OF PROGRESS
OUT OF NOWHERE.
COMING FROM BEHIND, MALCOLM
COMPLETES HIS MAZE, LIKE HE'D
DONE THIS MAZE 20 TIMES
THIS COULD BE A COME FROM
BEHIND!
MALCOLM WINS IMMUNITY!
MALCOLM, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR, AND AS FAR AS I KNOW YOU
STILL HAVE AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT HAS TO BE PLAYED TONIGHT.
IT GIVES YOU HUGE POWER GOING
INTO TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND AFTER 36 DAYS, LISA, SKUPIN,
ABI, DENISE, SOMEBODY GOING
HOME.
IT'S GOING TO BE A
DISAPPOINTMENT.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
>> KNOWING THAT MALCOLM WON AND
IT WASN'T ABI WAS A HUGE RELIEF.
TONIGHT IS A SLAM DUNK.
THERE WILL BE NO OTHER NAME I'M
WRITING DOWN OTHER THAN ABI'S
AND THE TORTURE OF DEALING WITH
HER WILL BE DONE.
>> YOU CAN GRILL INDIVIDUAL
PIECES.
THE FIRE IS DEFINITELY HOT
ENOUGH.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> IT GOT YOU THAT TIME.
>> JUST ONE LITTLE SPARK.
>> YOU CAN MOVE REALLY FAST.
>> I LOST TODAY, UNFORTUNATELY.
, TO MALCOLM.
IT'S DEVASTATING.
IT'S LIKE...
I'M TIRED.
I'M HUNGRY.
I'M EMOTIONALLY WEAK.
AND I GET NO CREDIT HERE.
BUT EVEN THOUGH I'M DRAINED, I
WILL KEEP ON FIGHTING.
SO I NEED SKUPIN AND LISA TO
VOTE WITH ME AGAINST DENISE.
I KNOW YOU GUYS ARE VOTE TALKING
ABOUT VOTING ME OFF TONIGHT.
THAT'S NOT A SECRET.
BUT I THINK IF YOU GUYS VOTE ME
OFF THAT'S GOING TO BE A
DISASTER.
YOU GUYS ARE NOT GOING TO HAVE A
CHANCE BETWEEN DENISE AND MOL
COM.
THEY HAVE SUCH A STORY.
HONESTLY, BRINGING ME TO FINAL
THREE, WITH YOU AND LISA, YOU
KNOW, I'VE BEEN VERY HUMBLE
HERE.
IT'S THE BEST CHANCE YOU HAVE AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
NO ONE IS GOING TO WANT TO VOTE
FOR ME.
>> YOU'D THINK IT WOULD BE AN
EASY DECISION TONIGHT.
IT'S NOT, BECAUSE EVERYTHING
MATTERS SO MUCH WHEN YOU GET
DOWN TO THE END GAME LIKE THIS.
AND YOU HAVE TO CONSIDER EVERY
SCENARIO IF YOU WANT TO COME OUT
ON TOP.
>> MY HEART'S TELLING ME IF YOU
GUYS TAKE DENISE OR MALCOLM,
THERE'S NO CHANCE.
>> THAT'S TRUE, PROBABLY.
I MEAN, IT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
I HAVE TO TALK TO LISA AND MAKE
SURE WHERE HER HEAD'S AT.
ABI HASN'T DONE MUCH THAT'S
LIKABLE AT ALL IN A GAME WHERE
EVERYBODY IS TRYING TO BE LIKED
BY EVERYBODY BUT HANGING OUT
WITH ABI THE NEXT THREE DAYS
WOULD DEFINITELY BE WORTH A
MILLION DOLLARS.
>> ARE WE ALONE?
>> MALCOLM'S DOWN AT THE ROCK.
WHERE IS DENISE?
>> GETTING COCONUTS
>> WHAT IS SHE SAYING?
>> ME, YOU AND HER IN THE FINAL
THREE.
>> REALLY?
REALLY? !
I LIKE, MICHAEL.
SHE MIGHT GET PETE AND ARTIS,
BUT THAT'S IT.
>> I KNOW.
>> HERE'S A QUESTION FOR YOU
TOTALLY ON THE SIDE.
FIVE IS THE LAST TIME YOU CAN
PLAY YOUR IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY CHANCE YOU'RE GIVING THAT
PUPPY UP?
>> IF THE SITUATION CALLED FOR
IT, BUT--
>> BUT THEY WOULDN'T KEEP ABI.
>> THEY WOULDN'T KEEP ABI.
>> YEAH, NO.
>> I'M DOUBLE PROTECTED AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
I'VE GOT THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE
FROM THE CHALLENGE, AND I'VE GOT
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IN MY
POCKET.
>> YEAH.
SO...
>> BUT I REALLY HAVE NO
INTENTION OF GIVING DENISE THE
IDOL.
THERE'S NO REASON TO.
SHE'S SAFE.
BECAUSE MYSELF, SKUPIN, DENISE,
AND LISA WILL ALL VOTE FOR ABI
TONIGHT.
SO IT MEANS MY MOM IS GOING TO
GET A NICE LITTLE SOMETHING TO
PUT ON THE SHELF FOR A LONG TIME
TO COME.
>> A, ABI, B, DENISE, C,
MALCOLM.
>> THE ONE PROBLEM IS IF MALCOLM
WINS IMMUNITY, AT THE FINAL
FOUR, YOU AND I ARE NOT
GUARANTEED THE FINAL THREE.
>> WE MAY NEED ME, YOU, AND
DENISE AGAINST MALCOLM AT THE
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
I WANT TO GO TO THE END WITH
ABI.
SOMEONE I FEEL IT WOULD BE
EASIER TO BEAT.
BUT MALCOLM WON THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE TODAY AND HE IS GETTING
MORE AND MORE TRUSS BY THE DAY.
HE COULD CONTINUE TO WIN
IMMUNITY ALL THE WAY UP TO THE
END, MAYBE THE WHOLE GAME.
HERE HE COMES, BY THE WAY.
>> TELL ME WHEN HE'S IN EAR
SHOT.
>> HE'S IN EAR SHOT NOW.
>> AND SO WE NEED ALL AVAILABLE
MANPOWER TO DEFEAT MALCOLM AT
THE FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
AND ABI'S NOT A SERIOUS
OPPONENT, SO WE MAY NEED DENISE
IN THERE TO KNOCK MALCOLM OUT OF
THERE.
SINCE MY BROTHER CAME OUT, HE
REALLY DID KIND OF RECALBRIGHT
ME.
TONIGHT'S DECISION FOR ME IT
BASED PURELY ON STRATEGY, PURELY
ON PLANNING OUTAL THE DIFFERENT
SCENARIOS, WHICH TRADEOFF IS
GOING TO COST ME THE MOST, AND
TRADEOFF IS GOING TO REWARD THE
MOST, AND THEN JUST HOPING THAT
I GUESSED RIGHT
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
R.C.
JEFF.
ARTIS, PETE.
PENNER
AND CHARTER, VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LISA, MALCOLM WINS IMMUNITY.
LAST I KNOW, HE STILL HAS AN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
WALK ME THROUGH WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN YOU GET BACK TO THE BEACH
TODAY.
>> WELL, IT WAS ABI PLAYING
"SURVIVOR" AND NOT GOING DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT, AND PRESENTING
SOME PRETTY STRONG ARGUMENTS.
>> Jeff: SO, ABI, YOU'RE
FEELING LIKE YOU'RE THE ONE IN
TROUBLE TONIGHT?
>> YES, MY BACK IS AGAINST THE
WALL.
>> Jeff: WITH RESPECT-- WHICH
PROBABLY MEANS WITHOUT ANY--
YOU'VE BEEN DETESTED, LAUGHED
AT, AND THEN TOLD YOU'RE NOT
LIKABLE, NOT A GOOD PERSON, HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH YOUR CULTURE,
YOU'RE JUST NOT NICE.
NOBODY HERE WANTS YOU AROUND.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'VE BEEN TOLD.
AND YET YOU MIGHT BE SOMEBODY
GOOD TO TAKE TO THE END.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IM THE BEST PERSON TO TAKE TO
THE END WITH THEM, BECAUSE
EVERYONE HERE CAN BEAT ME.
>> Jeff: DENISE, ABI'S MAKING
A PRETTY SIMPLE CASE.
>> DEFINITELY, IF THAT'S THE WAY
YOU WANT TO PLAY THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR," ABI IS THE PERFECT
PERSON TO TAKE BECAUSE YOU WANT
TO BRING SOMEBODY WHO TRULY
HASN'T OUTWITTED, OUTPLAYED, AND
OUTLASTED.
>> Jeff: YOU COULD MAKE AN
ARGUMENT THAT ABI AZOUTWITTED,
OUTPLAYED, AND OUTLASTED 13
PEOPLE IN THIS GAME.
>> YOU COULD ALSO SAY THERE WAS
SOME LUCK IN THAT.
TANDANG NEVER HAD TO GO THROUGH
THE TRIBAL CONSILS.
>> MY TANDANG COLORS ARE ABOUT
TO BURST.
I DON'T THINK IT WAS ALL LUCK
THAT WE NEVER WENT TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WE AVOIDED TRIKE NOT BECAUSE
OF LUCK, BUT BECAUSE OF THE
STRENGTH OF TANDANG.
SO--
>> YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT
ABSOLUTELY.
>> SO CLEAR THAT UP.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, AT WHAT
POINT ARE YOU ALREADY THINKING
WHO DO I WANT TO SIT NEXT TO AT
THE END?
>> WINNING THIS GAME NOW IS
STARTING TO TAKE OVER A LOT OF
MY THOUGHTS, AND I WANT IT AS
MUCH AS ANYBODY SITTING UP HERE.
SO, YEAH, WHO I THINK I CAN BEAT
IS DEFINITELY BEING CONSIDERED
RIGHT NOW.
>> EXCUSE ME.
I AM JUST LETTING YOU KNOW THAT
THEY CANNOT BEAT DENISE.
I'M JUST GOING TO SPEAK THE
TRUTH.
SHE'S MANIPULATIVE.
SHE'S REALLY GOOD WITH HER
WORDS.
AND SHE'S A PHYSICAL THREAT AS
WELL.
>> Jeff: SO, ABI, YOU THINK
DENISE COULD WIN THE GAME IF SHE
GETS TO THE END.
>> OH, YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
DENISE OR MALCOLM.
IT'S GOING TO BE ONE OF THE TWO.
LISA AND SKUPIN ARE NOT WINNING
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, WHAT'S YOUR
REACTION TO THAT?
>> YOU KNOW, JEFF, IT'S SO MANY
THINGS BECAUSE--
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE A MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> ANYWAY, JEFF, TO FINISH MY
THOUGHT--
>> YOU'RE A MORON.
>> WHAT IS THE REACTION, I DON'T
KNOW?
>> YOU ARE A MORON.
>> UNFORTUNATELY --
>> HOLD ON, ABI CALLED YOU AN
IDIOT ONCE AND A MORON TWICE.
>> IT'S JUST, I THINK SO HER WAY
OF COMMUNICATING.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
>> HE THINKS HE'S GOING TO WIN A
MILLION DOLLARS AT THE END.
HE'S NOT.
>> Jeff: LISA, IS THERE ANY
STRATEGY THAT WOULD SAY, YOU
KNOW, THE MORE THAT ABI TALKS,
THE BETTER MY CHANCES?
AND RATHER THAN SEND HER OVER
THERE ON THE JURY, I'LL JUST
KEEP HER NEXT TO ME?
>> ABSOLUTELY, AND I HAVE NOT
BEEN ASHAMED TO SAY OR APOLOGIZE
THAT I WOULD TAKE SOMEBODY TO BE
EASIER TO BEAT THAN NOBLER TO
BEAT IN THE END FOR A MILLION
DOLLARS.
AND I MEAN THAT.
>> AND I WOULD BE THE ONLY
PERSON THAT YOU COULD BEAT.
>> Jeff: SO IF YOU CAN'T WIN,
WHY DO YOU CARE JAI CAME THIS
FAR.
I WOULD LIKE TO AT LEAST MAKE IT
TO FINAL THREE.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, YOU'RE A FAN
OF THE GAME.
THAT HAS WORKED FOR OTHER
PEOPLE.
>> YEAH, AND IT'S WORKED
STRAIGHT TO A MILLION DOLLARS
BEFORE IN THIS GAME.
SO IF YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE ABI
BECAUSE SHE'S A GOAT, BE
PREPARED SHE'S NOT GOING TO GO
DOWN WITHOUT A FIGHT AND SHE
COULD DEFINITELY STILL PULL THIS
THING OFF.
>> Jeff: ABI, IS IT FAIR TO
CALL YOU A LOUD MOUTH?
>> I GUESS SO, YEAH.
I'VE BEEN A LOUD MOUTH.
>> Jeff: AND IS BEING A LOUD
MOUTH A BAD THING OR IS THAT
JUST HOW I'M PLAYING "SURVIVOR."
>> IT'S NOT AD ABOUT THING.
IT'S HOW I'M PLAYING "SURVIVOR."
DENISE, SHE'S PLAYING LIKE SHE'S
THE ELITE, THE BEST OF THE BEST.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN ME AND
HER.
I'M HERE FOR A MILLION DOLLARS,
I NEED IT.
SHE'S HERE TO MAKE FRIENDS,
CLEARLY.
>> NO, I'M HERE FOR A MILLION
DOLLARS, THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE.
>> Jeff: OKAY, SO AS WE HEAD
INTO ANOTHER VERY BIG VOTE, IT
SEEMS LIKE IT IS EITHER ABI OR
DENISE.
LET'S FIND OUT WHICH WAY IT IS
GOING TO GO.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ABI, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU ARE PATRONIZING,
JUDGMENTAL.
YOU ARE JUST NOT A GOOD PERSON.
I REALLY DON'T LIKE YOU.
>> ABI IF THIS VOTE DOESN'T GO
AS PLANNED THERE'S SOMETHING
SERIOUSLY WRONG IN THE UNIVERSE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, DENISE
ABI.
TWO VOTES ABE ONE VOTE DENISE.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SEVENTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ABI.
THAT'S THREE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD LUCK TO ALL OF YOU.
>> Jeff: ABI, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO
WELL, AFTER 36 DAYS IT, COMES
DOWN TO THIS, TWO ORIGINAL
TANDANG, TWO ORIGINAL MATSING.
IT'S A SHOWDOWN AND SOMETHING'S
ABOUT TO GIVE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> THIS SUNDAY, ON A SPECIAL
TWO-HOUR SEASON FINALE.
>> FINAL FOUR.
>> Jeff: A PACT THAT TOOK
THESE FOUR SURVIVORS THIS FAR.
BUT WITH A MILLION DOLLARS ON
THE LINE, ALLIANCES WILL BE
SHATTERED.
>> I MEAN, ARE WE STILL GOOD?
DIDN'T SHAKE HER HAND.
DIDN'T GIVE HER MY WORD.
>> SUNDAY, DECEMBER 16.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, THINGS DIDN'T
GO MY WAY.
AFTER THE MERGE, I WAS TARGETED
AS THE CRAZY LATINA, AND
SOMETIMES I COME OFF REALLY
DIRECT AND STRAIGHT TO THE
POINT, BUT THAT'S THE TYPE OF
PERSON I AM.
I DON'T BEAT AROUND THE BUSH.