>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR" -- THIS SEASON THERE
ARE THREE TRIBES, BUT MATSING IS
THE ONLY TRIBE ON ITS TRY
EXTINCTION.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
RUSSELL'S CLUE AND AN ALLIANCE
BETWEEN MALCOLM AND DENICE WERE
ALL THEY HAD TO SHOW AFTER THE
FIRST SIX DAYS.
>> THE TRIBE OF SIX IS ALREADY
DOWN TO FOUR.
>> Jeff: AT TANDANG PETE
STIRRED THINGS UP BY STARTING A
NEW MAJORITY ALLIANCE.
>> WE HAVE THREE VOTES, YOU,
ARTIS AND ABI.
>> Jeff: TURNING ON HIS OLD
ALLIANCE AND GIVING LISA THE
FORMER TEEN STAR NEW LIFE.
>> I HAVE TO PLAY THE HAND I
HAVE THAT.
SO TODAY I'M UP.
>> Jeff: THINGS ONLY GOT
BETTER FOR PETE WHEN HIS ALLY
ABI SHARED THE KPHAOU AND FOUND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I'M PAYING ATTENTION TO
EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: AT KALABAW, PENNER
HAD BEEN THE TARGET FROM DAY
ONE.
>> DO WE WANT A VETERAN TO WIN
OR ONE OF US TO WIN?
>> Jeff: BUT WHEN HE REVEALED
HIS IDOL TO JEFF KENT, THE
FORMER PROFESSIONAL BASEBALL
PLAYER CONSIDERED ALIGNING WITH
PENNER.
>> I'LL TRY TO BEFRIEND HIM.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT'S BEST
FOR ME.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE ANGIE -- ANGIE
STRUGGLING.
AND RUSSELL STRUGGLED, LEADING
TO ANOTHER MATSING LOSS.
MATSING GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
FOR THE THIRD STRAIGHT TIME!
AND AT TRIBAL COUNCIL ANGIE AND
RUSSELL TOOK TURNS THROWING EACH
OTHER UNDER THE BUS.
>> THE SECOND TIME HE WENT IN HE
COMPLETELY GAVE UP.
>> WHEN YOU CAME BACK YOU WERE
DONE!
>> Jeff: DESPITE MALCOLM'S
CLOSE CONNECTION TO ANGIE, HE
JOINED MATSING IN VOTING TO KEEP
THE TRIBE STRONG.
>> THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> KICK SOME ASS.
>> Jeff: HOPEFULLY REMAINS IS
THE RIGHT COMBINATION OF PEOPLE
TO TURN THIS TRIBE AROUND.
15 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW, YOU GO 0-3 IN YOUR
FIRST THREE IMMUNITY CHALLENGES,
WAKE UP THE NEXT MORNING AND
IT'S POURING RAIN AND YOUR
FIRE'S OUT.
IT'S JUST LIKE WHAT ELSE COULD
YOU POSSIBLY PILE ON?
I WAS JUST THINKING, OH, WAIT,
WE HAVE COLD RICE.
(LAUGHTER)
I THINK WE ALL PUT ON BRAVE
FACES FOR EACH OTHER.
EVERYONE'S SCARED, EVERYONE'S
NERVOUS.
BUT ONE WIN IS ALL IT'S GOING TO
TAKE TO TURN THE MOOD AROUND
CAMP.
JUST ONE WIN TO KNOW THAT IT'S
POSSIBLE THAT WE'RE NOT JUST
DESTINED FOR ANNIHILATION.
>> HAVING THREE PEOPLE IN A
TRIBE, YOU KNOW, AT DAY NINE?
THIS IS NOT WHAT I ENVISIONED AT
ALL.
>> SITTING IN OUR SHELT THEY ARE
MORNING, THE RAIN'S COMING DOWN
AND THE THREE OF US ARE IN THERE
AND WE'RE MAKING JOKES AND THERE
HAVING CONVERSATIONS BUT YOU'LL
GET THAT SILENCE AND MY THOUGHTS
AREN'T ON LIKE, OH, MISSING
HOME.
MY THOUGHTS ARE ON HOW DO I STAY
HERE?
WHO'S GOING HOME?
AND IN COLLEGE I DID HAVE
ROOMMATES AND WE HAD THREE AND
WITH THREE THERE'S ALWAYS ONE
THAT'S OUT.
THE MINUTE I DON'T TAKE ALL MY
STUFF TO TRIBAL COUNCIL WILL BE
THE NIGHT I'M PROBABLY GOING
HOME.
>> LET'S JUST MOUNT THE GREATEST
COMEBACK EVER.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE'RE GONNA.
>> GONNA HAVE TO.
>> NOT AN OPTION.
IT'S NOT AN OPTION NOT TO.
>> ONE CHALLENGE AT A TIME.
MY PLAN IS WITH DENICE AND
MALCOLM TO MOUNT THE GREATEST
COMEBACK THAT'S EVER BEEN SEEN.
THERE IS NO QUIT IN EITHER ONE
OF THEM.
THERE DAMN SURE ISN'T ANY QUIT
FOR ME BECAUSE I WAS WILLING TO
DIE FOR THIS DAMN GAME THE LAST
TIME I PLAYED IT.
SO LINE IT UP, LET'S GO AND
WE'LL LET THE CHIPS FALL WHERE
THEY MAY.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> HALF THE TIME WE'VE BEEN HERE
WE'VE BEEN SITTING IN THE RAIN.
>> IS THERE ANY WAY WE CAN START
A FIRE?
>> IT'S RAINING!
>> YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE NOTHING TO
DO OUT HERE BUT THINK ABOUT
DIFFERENT SCENARIOS AND HOW THEY
MIGHT GO.
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT'S RAINING
NONSTOP AND FOR PEOPLE WHO COME
ON TO "SURVIVOR," YOU'RE USUALLY
GOING TO BE A TYPE-A PERSON
WHO'S USUALLY ABLE TO TAKE THE
WORLD BY THE NOSE AND MAKE IT
HAPPEN.
AND I'M JUST WORRIED THAT THE
RAIN MAY PROVE ONCE AGAIN THAT
WE ARE NOT ULTIMATELY IN
CONTROL.
>> ARE YOU READY, MAGNESIUM BOY?
MAKE IT GOOD, ARTIS, BECAUSE
WE'RE ONLY DOING IT ONE TIME.
THERE WE GO.
HERE IT COMES.
>> THE WEATHER SUCKS BUT I'M
FEELING REALLY GOOD.
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN A VERY, VERY,
VERY GOOD POSITION IN THIS GAME
AND I PLAN ON CREATING A LOT OF
CHAOS OUT HERE.
ANY CHAOS THAT I CREATE IS GOING
TO BE BENEFICIAL TO ME.
>> STARTING TO RAIN AGAIN.
>> WANT TO WAIT FOR THE RAIN TO
PASS?
>> WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT'S IN THAT BAG?
>> IT'S THE CLUE.
>> IT'S MY HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I WAS JUST STARING AT THE
RAFT WHERE WE SLEEP AND I SAW A
LITTLE PIECE OF PAPER STICKING
OUT.
IT'S THE CLUE THAT R.C. AND I
HAVE SAFELY BEEN GUARDING.
>> YOU WANT TO READ IT?
>> "AN IDOL LAYS IN WAITING
SOMEWHERE NEAR YOUR BEACH.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE PROTECTION
FROM FRIENDS AND FROM FOES.
IT COULD JUST BE SALVATION IS
RIGHT UNDER YOUR NOSE."
UNDER YOUR NOSE?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> I THINK SHE WENT, GOT THE
CLUE OUT OF WHERE WE HAD BURIED
IT, PUT IT IN HER BAG AND I
THINK IT FELL.
>> YOU FOUND IT HERE?
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> SHE HAS NO IDEA THAT I FOUND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, BUT I
DON'T FEEL BAD BECAUSE ME
FINDING THAT CLUE PROVED TO ME
THAT SHE WASN'T 100% HONEST WITH
ME AT ALL.
I'M REALLY SURPRISED THAT I SAW
THIS CLUE STICKING OUT OF YOUR
BAG.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THE CLUE.
>> MAYBE THE RATS BROUGHT IT
OVER.
>> I CERTAINLY DIDN'T PUT IT
THERE BUT BECAUSE THIS POPPED UP
I'M A LITTLE WEARY OF MY PLACE
RIGHT NOW IN THE TRIBE.
>> R.C. DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
I WAS THE ONE WHO PUT IT THERE.
ABI SHOWED ME WHERE THE CLUE TO
THE IDOL WAS SO I GOT IT, PUT IN
THE MY POCKET, R.C.'S BAG
SPILLED ALL OVER THE BED AND I
WAS LIKE -- AND THEN BOOM, CLUE
PLANTED.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THIS COULD HAVEN'T GONE ANY
BETTER.
THIS IS AMAZING.
IT'S HILARIOUS.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS JUST
CREATE A LITTLE CHAOS BECAUSE
KEEPING PEOPLE ON THEIR TOES IS
A BIG PART OF MY STRATEGY.
I DON'T WANT ANYBODY TO BE ABLE
TO PLAY THEIR GAME.
I WANT THEM TO PLAY MY GAME.
>> GETTING READY TO FISH?
>> YUP, I'M GETTING READY.
>> YOU WANT TO FISH OR YOU WANT
TO FIRE, CARTER?
THE RAIN WAS REALLY DEBILITATING
BUT WHEN THE SUN COMES OUT, MAN,
AND YOU FIND YOURSELF IN A
TROPICAL PARADISE!
I MEAN, THIS IS THE MOST
EXTRAORDINARY PLACE I'VE EVER
BEEN.
SO WE SAID OKAY, LET'S GET BUSY.
LET'S GET WORKING.
>> IS THIS A FIRE OFFICIALLY?
AM I DONE MAKING IT?
JEFF, IS THIS A FIRE?
>> TELL HER THE SECRET OF THE
FIRE.
>> WE'VE GOT A REALLY YOUNG
GROUP OF KIDS THAT AREN'T
MARRIED, THAT DON'T KNOW HOW TO
CARRY PROFESSIONAL CONVERSATION.
JONATHAN CAN DO THAT.
YOU KNOW, AND HE'S TRYING, YOU
KNOW?
THE GUY'S TRYING.
>> WE'RE GOING TO JUST PICK THEM
UP UNDERNEATH THIS BOAT RIGHT
HERE IS THE BIGGEST CLAM YOU
EVER SAW.
PICK IT UP.
(LAUGHS)
THAT'S AS BIG AS YOUR HEAD, MAN!
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE RIGHT THERE,
GRAB HER.
>> FROM THE GET-GO WHEN WE HAD
JONATHAN ON OUR RAFT I ALWAYS
HAD AN IDEA.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF IT WAS
JONATHAN OR RUSSELL OR SKUPIN, I
DIDN'T WANT A VESSEL -- VETERAN
TO WIN THIS GAME.
JONATHAN HAS THE IDOL, I WANT TO
GET FURTHER IN THIS GAME SO WE
HAVE TO MAKE ADJUSTMENTS.
>> UNLESS YOU THINK YOU'VE GOT
VALUE OUTSIDE OUR TRIPE, I CAN
BRING YOU VALUE IN OUR TRIBE
THROUGH ME.
>> EXACTLY.
>> I THINK YOU BRING YOURSELF
AND YOUR VETERAN STATUS AND THE
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I TOTALLY AGREED.
>> AND I THINK I'VE GOT A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP WITH OUR GUYS AND
OBVIOUSLY CARTER IS ONE OF THEM
AND I CAN CONTROL SOME PEOPLE.
>> AWESOME.
AWESOME.
I HEAR YOU.
JEFF AND I ACTUALLY LIKE EACH
OTHER AND HE'S A HELL OF A
COMPETITOR, A REALLY NICE GUY
AND HE AND I ARE PREPARED TO BE
LOYAL TO EACH OTHER DEEP INTO
THE GAME.
>> LET'S RIDE TOGETHER AND SEE
WHERE WE GO.
>> GREAT.
>> AND AFTER THE END --
>> WE'RE GONNA GO FAR.
>> ALL RIGHT, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
>> HAVING HIM ON MY SIDE, AT
LEAST FOR THE TIME BEING, WILL
MAKE US BOTH PRETTY, PRETTY
POWERFUL.
IT'S EXCITING.
IT'S EXCITING TO HAVE A REAL
ALLY.
I THINK I DO.
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING TO MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE A -- YOUNG MAN WHO'S NOT
GOING TO BE TRUE TO HIS WORD.
>> YEAH.
>> AND DOESN'T WANT TO PLAY A
STRAIGHT-UP GAME.
>> I DO WANT TO PLAY A STRAIGHT
UP GAME.
I WANT TO GET FAR.
I'M JUST THINKING THAT YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO GET THAT FAR IF
YOU'RE ALIGNED WITH DAWSON AND
KATIE.
RIGHT NOW I WANT TO GO FAR WITH
YOU.
>> THANK YOU, MAN.
>> IT'S KIND OF CRAZY BECAUSE I
DECIDED THAT JONATHAN WAS NO
LONGER A TARGET OF MINE BUT
SOMEBODY THAT I WAS GOING TO
WORK WITH AND TRY TO GET TO THE
TOP FIVE WITH HIM AND THEN
TARGET HIM.
SO I'D SAY ME, JEFF, AND
JONATHAN RIGHT NOW HAVE A PRETTY
GOOD ALLIANCE AND THE GIRLS FOR
ALL I CAN TELL ARE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> IT WAS A DEMOCRACY IN THE
BEGINNING BUT NOW IT'S A
DEMOCRACY BETWEEN THEM THREE.
>> AT THE BEGINNING OF THE GAME
THERE WAS OUR FIVE-PERSON
ALLIANCE OF THE -- YOU KNOW,
BRAND NEW CASTAWAYS AND THEN
THERE WAS JONATHAN ON THE OTHER
END AND WE WERE KIND OF WORKING
TO GET HIM OUT.
BUT THE GUYS WENT OUT ON TO THE
OCEAN AND THEY WERE OUT THERE
FOR A COUPLE HOURS AND, OF
COURSE, WHAT ARE THEY TALKING
ABOUT?
JUST THEM IN THE WATER?
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT US!
>> I THINK PROBABLY THE BEST
THING FOR US TO DO IS STICK
TOGETHER AND WHEN WE MERGE TRY
TO WORK WHATEVER MAGIC WE CAN
AND THEN WE'LL TRY TO GATHER IN
SOME MORE LADIES AND HOW AWESOME
WOULD THAT BE AS A STRATEGY?
I'M A GIRL, I CAN MAKE FIRE, I
CAN KILL A CHICKEN.
DOESN'T MATTER.
WE DON'T NEED THEM.
>> I THINK WOMEN NATURALLY FEEL
MORE COMFORTABLE AROUND EACH
OTHER.
AS THE GAME PROGRESSES I THINK
THE SEX STARTS TO SPLIT A LITTLE
AND, YOU KNOW, THE GUYS HAVE
THIS STRICT THING THAT THEY
THINK THAT THIS IS WHAT THEY ADD
TO THE TABLE AND WOMEN
DEFINITELY THINK WELL, I HAVE
THIS AWESOME SOCIAL GAME AND
THIS ADDS TO THE TABLE.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME BECAUSE
I'M A FEMALE.
THAT'S THE WORST THING YOU CAN
DO TO A WOMAN.
>> IT'S ABOUT TO GET CRAZY.
OF OUR TRIBE -- AND THEY WERE
LIKE ALMOST USELESS.
(LAUGHS)
OH, THIS GAME, I TELL YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, NOT MAKE THE MERGE?
GOSH, THAT WOULD JUST SUCK.
>> YUP.
>> BECAUSE OF A SMOKER, A
LUNATIC, AND A BEAUTY QUEEN.
(LAUGHS)
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK I SIZED
RUSS UP PRETTY GOOD RIGHT OFF
THE BAT.
HE'S MET MY LOW EXPECTATIONS THE
ENTIRE WAY THROUGH.
HE'S BEEN FOISTED TWICE NOW INTO
A POSITION OF LEADERSHIP AND IT
WORKED OUT ONCE IN SAMOA FOR
HIM.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, UNTIL HE
COLLAPSED.
YOU CAN TELL WATCHING HIM THAT
HE LACKED SELF-AWARENESS.
FROM DAY ONE.
AND IT'S APPARENT IN CHALLENGES,
APPARENT IN THE WAY HE TALKS TO
US AROUND CAMP.
IT'S APPARENT WHEN HE LOSES HIS
COOL AT TRIBAL FOR NO REASON.
HE'S STILL HERE ONLY BECAUSE
WE'RE DOING SO BADLY AND WE NEED
MUSCLE MASS.
>> SO, I MEAN, IN TERMS OF
SLEEPING ARRANGEMENTS, FOOD, ALL
THAT STUFF, GREAT.
GAME PLAY?
SUCKS.
BECAUSE, YEAH, EVERYBODY'S
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW IT'S
NOT GONNA BE THEM.
BUT THE UNFORTUNATE PART IS
NEITHER ONE OF THEM HAS SAID
ANYTHING TO ME ABOUT WHERE THEY
WANT TO GO IN THE EVENT THAT THE
BOTTOM FALLS OUT OF THIS THING
AND THAT MAKES ME A LITTLE
SUSPICIOUS.
>> SO I HAVE A CLUE TO WHERE THE
IDOL IS HIDDEN AND UNTIL MY
TORTURE YOU HAVE?
I WILL BE TRYING TO FIND THAT
IDOL BECAUSE THERE'S NO QUESTION
ABOUT IT: I'M PROBABLY GONNA
NEED IT.
THE CLUE READS SOMETHING LIKE--
AND I LOVE THIS WORD "SOMEWHERE
NEAR YOUR BEACH IT'S RIGHT
BEFEAT YOUR NOSE."
THE REAL FRUSTRATING PART IS I
HAVE A FEELING THAT I'VE BEEN
LIKE PAST THIS THING LIKE A
HUNDRED MILLION TIMES IT'S LIKE
RIGHT THERE AND THEN EVERYBODY'S
GONNA SEE, THERE'S GONNA BE,
LIKE, THIS FLASH ON THE SCREEN
AND THEY'RE GONNA BE LIKE THIS
DUMMY!
HE'S WALKING PAST IT.
AND IT JUST SUCKS.
>> I'M TRYING TO FIND THE STUPID
IDOL.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS SOMETHING
THAT FELL DOWN BUT IT WAS JUST
LIKE SOMETHING THAT WAS ALREADY
BLOWN.
>> WENT UP THE BEACH WHEN WE HAD
A MOMENTARY BREAK IN THE RAIN,
GATHERED SOME WOOD AND CAME
AROUND THE CORNER AND I DON'T
KNOW WHY, BUT JUST -- IT JUST
SEEMED A LITTLE SHADY.
RUSSELL WAS AT THE VERY CORNER
OF THE -- OF OUR SHELTER AND HE
WAS PUTTING A BANANA LEAF THERE
AND HE KIND OF SAID LIKE --
>> THEN I SAW A POPL -- I MEAN A
BANANA LEAF BLOW AND I'M LIKE
DID THAT JUST COME FROM THERE SO
I WAS LIKE LET ME GO AND SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> I DON'T KNOW BUT IT
DEFINITELY KIND OF PLANTED A
LITTLE SEED OF "WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?"
>> IT WAS JUST KIND OF -- I
DON'T KNOW.
IT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
>> I WAS TALKING TO DENICE AND
SHE HAD THIS SCARED LOOK HER IN
KWAI AND TELLS ME SHE THINKS
RUSSELL HAS AN IDOL AND I GUESS
SHE SAW HIM DIGGING AROUND THE
CORNER OF THE SHELTER.
SO AFTER DENICE TELLS ME ALL
THIS, THE LOGICAL THING IS IF
YOU BUSTED HIM WHILE HE WAS
HIDING IT, HE JUST STUCK IN THE
HIS POCKET.
SO ME AND DENICE WENT THROUGH
ALL OF HIS STUFF IN THE SHELTER.
I MEAN, I HAVE NO SHAME OUT
HERE.
IF YOU HAVE AN IDOL, I WANT TO
KNOW ABOUT IT.
I WANT AS MANY VARIABLES IN MY
CONTROL AS POSSIBLE.
IT WASN'T IN HIS CLOTHES, WASN'T
IN HIS SHOES, WASN'T IN HIS BAG.
THERE'S NO REASON TO TAKE A
RISK.
MIGHT AS WELL JUST BLIND SIDE
HIM AND, YOU KNOW, LEAVE NO ROOM
FOR ERROR.
>> YOU KEEP BOILING RICE, ABI?
>> YEAH, YOU BOIL IT.
>> BUT AFTER IT'S BOILING YOU
KEEP IT BOILING?
>> YOU KEEP BOILING IT UNTIL
THERE'S NO WATER LEFT.
>> I THINK WE NEED MORE WATER,
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
>> IF YOU NEED TO ADD MORE WATER
THAN YOU'VE GOT TO ADD MY SALT.
>> I DON'T WANT IT TO BE TOO
SALTY.
TASTE THIS, YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
>> I THINK IT NEEDS MORE SALT,
BUT YOU KNOW ME, I'M A SALTY
PERSON.
>> IT'S LIKE A HOME-COOKED MEAL.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANKS FOR
HELPING, R.C.
THERE WAS ALREADY A WEDGE
BETWEEN R.C. AND ABI BUT NOW
IT'S CONCRETE AND IT ALL COMES
FROM ONE PIECE OF PAPER.
I WOULD LOVE TO SEND KWRAEURS
HOME RIGHT R.C. HOME RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T TRUST R.C.
SHE IS DANGEROUS.
BUT SHE HAS ONE BIG PROBLEM: I'M
HERE.
>> DO YOU WANT TO TALK AT ALL
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY?
>> I REALLY DON'T.
I HAVE NOTHING TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT, I'M OVER IT, I MOVED ON.
>> I KNOW BUT BECAUSE WE --
>> I DON'T.
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP ON TALKING
TO ME, MOVE ON, I'M SERIOUS,
STOP.
MOVE ON.
I'M NOT GOING TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT ANYTHING YOU KNOW WHAT YOU
DID.
>> I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
>> I DO NOT WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU DID.
YOU BROKE -- YOU BETRAYED ME.
YOU BROKE MY TRUST.
SO THAT'S IT.
DON'T EVEN GO THERE.
>> THAT'S WHY WE NEED TO TALK
ABI.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
I HAVE NOTHING TO TALK TO YOU.
>> FINE, WE WON'T TALK.
>> YEAH, I DON'T WANT TO.
>> ABI IS IRRATIONAL.
SHE'S NOT RATIONAL.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE'S
THINKING.
>> I NEED TO GO FOR A WALK.
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT MY PLACE IN
THE TRIBE BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T
WANT TO TALK TO ME ABOUT THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY CLUE.
I DON'T KNOW IF SHE PLANTED IT,
I HAVE NO IDEA.
PETE, WHAT THE HELL IS SHE
TALKING ABOUT?
>> I WASN'T HERE.
>> YOU HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO CLUE
WHY SHE WON'T TALK TO ME?
>> NO, THAT'S BETWEEN YOU GUYS,
NOT ME.
>> YOU'RE LYING TO ME BY NOT
TELLING ME.
>> WHATEVER YOU WANT TO BELIEVE
IS WHAT YOU WANT TO BELIEVE.
>> I THOUGHT I HAD IT LOCKED
DOWN.
I THOUGHT I HAD ABI AS MY
NUMBER.
TWO I THOUGHT I HAD PETE.
I THINK I'M IN TKAEUPBGER IF
THERE'S AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
AND I LOSE.
>> IF I KNEW WHAT I DID WRONG I
COULD APOLOGIZE AND INSTEAD IT'S
THIS BLOWUP AGAIN OF NOTHING.
>> I DON'T KNOW, EITHER.
>> IT CAN'T JUST BE ME
CONSTANTLY SAYING "LET'S TALK
ABOUT THIS, LET'S GET OVER IT,
LET'S MOVE ON."
WE NEED TO BE UNITED.
WE NEED TO BE A TEAM.
>> I THINK THE STRAW THAT BROKE
THE CAMEL'S BACK WAS WHEN R.C.
LET THE CLUE OUT OF HER BAG AND
ABI'S LITTLE BRAZILIAN SPICE
JUST BROKE OPEN.
>> SHE'S LIKE TOO MUCH.
SHE'S JUST LIKE -- SERIOUSLY,
ARE YOU INSULTING MY
INTELLIGENCE RIGHT NOW?
YOU'RE TRYING TO FRIGGING FOOL
ME?
I'M NOT STUPID.
>> SO MORE OF MY ENERGY IS GOING
TO GO INTO JUST BLOWING A LITTLE
OXYGEN ON SOME FIRE OVER HERE
AND LET THEM FLAME OUT FOR ME SO
THAT I DON'T HAVE TO BE THE ONE
THAT TAKES THE HEAT.
KALABAW AND TANDANG GETTING YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW MATSING
TRIBE.
ANGIE VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THING'S FIRST,
I'LL TAKE BACK THE IDOLS.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ONE AT A
TIME YOU WILL CARRY TWO POTS OF
RICE ON A BAMBOO POLE THROUGH A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
YOU'LL PLACE THE POTS IN THEIR
STAND AND HEAD BACK, THEN THE
NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL SIX
POTS, YOU WILL USE A WRECKING
BALL TO SMASH THE POTS.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO SMASH ALL
SIX POTS WIN IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM
THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL KOUPB JILL
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
ONCE AGAIN YOU ARE ALSO PLAYING
FOR REWARD.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH --
(ALL GASPS).
>> Jeff: STEAK, VEGGIES,
SPICES, ALL THE UTENSILS YOU
NEED FOR A NICE MALE AND A GREAT
SOURCE OF PROTEIN.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH.
COUPLE OF VEGGIES, SALT AND
PEPPER AND A POT TO COOK IT IN.
AND IF EITHER WINNING TRIBE
WANTS TO TRADE IN THEIR REWARD
FOR A TARP YOU CAN STILL DO SO.
BECAUSE MATSING IS DOWN TO THREE
TRIBE MEMBERS, KALABAW, TANDANG,
HALF YOUR TRIBE HAS TO SIT OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
WHO'S IT GONNA BE?
>> THE THREE LADIES ARE GONNA
SIT OUT.
>> WE'RE GONNA SIT THE THREE
LADIES, TOO, JEFF.
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES SITTING
OUT THE WOMEN.
THE MEN ARE GONNA RUN IT.
SIT-OUTS TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A BIG REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
MALCOLM OUT FIRST FOR MATSING,
SKUPIN FOR TANDANG AND CARTER
FOR KALABAW.
MALCOLM OFF TO A QUICK START,
SKUPIN OUT THERE.
CARTER BREAKS A POT!
HE'S GOT TO LOAD ANOTHER ONE.
MALCOLM OFF TO A FAST START FOR
MATSING.
SKUPIN NOW SLOWING DOWN.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME!
>> Jeff: CARTIER TRYING TO GET
BACK IN THIS.
MATSING, FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
ANY CHALLENGE, IS IN THE LEAD.
SKUPIN RIGHT BEHIND.
CARTER HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE!
HE LOST A POT RIGHT OFF THE BAT
AND NOW HE'S STRUGGLING.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM HEADING BACK.
MALCOLM FLYING THROUGH THE
COURSE FOR MATSING.
RUSSELL NOW ON THE COURSE FOR
MATSING.
CARTER TRYING TO MAKE UP SOME
TIME NOW FOR KALABAW.
THERE'S ARTIS FOR TANDANG.
THIS IS A CHALLENGE THAT MAY GO
QUICKLY, SO FALLING BEHIND CAN
GET YOU IN TROUBLE.
ARTIS REALLY TAKING HIS TIME FOR
TANDANG.
CARTER'S NOW BACK.
HERE COMES PENNER FOR KALABAW!
RUSSELL HEADS BACK TO MATSING.
MATSING STILL IN THE LEAD.
PENNER TRYING TO MAKE UP SOME
GROUND AND HE IS!
ARTIS HAVING TROUBLE.
HIS LONG LEGS GETTING THERE
THIS, SCRAPING HIS BACK AGAINST
THAT OBSTACLE.
DENICE NOW HEADING OUT WITH THE
FINAL TWO POTS OF RICE.
MATSING STILL IN THE LEAD.
THE FINAL TWO POTS OF RICE FOR
TANDANG.
KALABAW HAS PICKED UP TIME, JEFF
NOW HEADING OUT FROM KALABAW.
PETE HAS NOW TAKEN THE LEAD FOR
TANDANG!
DENICE NOW STARTING TO FALL
BEHIND.
>> YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
WE'RE DOING FINE!
>> Jeff: HERE COMES JEFF
COMING OUT WITH THE LAST TWO
POTS FOR KALABAW.
GRABBING BOTH POTS AT ONCE.
>> COME ON, MAMA!
>> Jeff: DENICE TRIES FOR TWO
BUT CAN'T DO IT, THESE POTS ARE
HEAVY AND BIG.
PETE HEADS BACK.
SLOWLY KALABAW IS GAINING ON
MATSING.
JEFF IS NOW CATCHING DENICE.
>> COME ON, DENICE!
DIG DEEP!
>> Jeff: GO, TANDANG!
EVERYBODY UNDER THE OBSTACLE.
TANDANG WITH THE LEAD, THEY'RE
NOW HEADING OUT TOWARDS THE
FINAL STAGE OF THIS CHALLENGE.
THIS IS IT!
MATSING IS NOW BACK.
THEY'RE HEADING OUT FOR THE
FINAL STAGE OF THIS CHALLENGE.
KALABAW DESPERATELY TRYING TO
CATCH UP.
HUSTLE UP, KALABAW!
>> COME ON, MAN!
>> THEY'RE BACK, WHO'S GONNA DO
IT?
ARTIS IS GONNA BE THE ONE
SMASHING POTS.
MALCOLM GONNA BE THE ONE
SMASHING POTS FOR MATSING.
KALABAW'S BACK!
HUSTLE OUT, YOU HAVE TO GET
THROUGH THIS OBSTACLE!
TANDANG WITH A NICE SMASH!
ARTIS DOING A GREAT JOB.
>> COME ON, MALCOLM!
>> Jeff: KALABAW'S BACK!
YOU GUYS ARE STILL IN THIS!
>> ANYBODY'S GAME!
(SCREAMING)
>> Jeff: POT SMASHING ALL OVER
THE PLACE.
TANDANG LOOKING FOR ONE LAST
POT.
MATSING DOWN TO TWO POTS LEFT.
ANOTHER POT OUT.
FOUR POTS LEFT FOR KALABAW.
ARTIS FOR THE WIN.
(SCREAMING)
TANDANG WINS IMMUNITY AND STEAK
REWARD!
WE'RE STILL GOING FOR SECOND.
KALABAW DOWN TO TWO POTS LEFT.
MATSING ONE POT LEFT!
KALABAW ONE POT LEFT!
THIS IS IT!
MALCOLM MISSES!
JEFF MISSES!
MATSING SO CLOSE THEY CAN TASTE
IT.
MALCOLM MISSES AGAIN!
JEFF CAN WIN IT!
(SCREAMING).
>> Jeff: KALABAW WINS IMMUNITY
AND REWARD!
MATSING LOSES FOR THE FOURTH
STRAIGHT TIME!
HUGE COMEBACK FROM KALABAW.
>> YOU DID GREAT.
>> THAT WAS KILLER.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> SAME OLD CRAP!
>> OH, WELL.
>> SAME OLD!
LORD, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED!
YOU GAVE ME ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY,
I DON'T GET WHAT'S HAPPENING,
FATHER, YOU'VE GOT TO HELP ME
UNDERSTAND THIS.
I JUST CAN'T TAKE THIS!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, YOU'VE BEEN
GOING ON BREAKING POTS, TALKING
TO I DON'T KNOW WHO, IF YOU'RE
TALKING TO GOD --
>> I'M TALKING TO GOD, LORD -- I
MEAN, JEFF.
YOU KNOW, FOR ME, THIS ISN'T
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, WITH ALL DUE
RESPECT, YOU SOMETIMES TALK LIKE
YOU'RE A SUPERHERO.
LIKE SUPERMAN'S NEVER SUPPOSED
TO FAIL.
YOU'RE JUST A GUY!
>> I'M A GUY WHO WAS FORMED BY
GOD'S HANDS.
I'M A PERFECT CREATURE AND AS
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED THAT'S THE
WAY I'M SUPPOSED TO LIVE MY
LIFE: IN EXCELLENCE!
AND EVERYTHING I'M SUPPOSED TO
DO IS SUPPOSED TO BE EXCELLENT.
>> Jeff: AND THAT MEANS NEVER
FAILING?
>> RIGHT.
RIGHT!
ABSOLUTELY!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, NOT EVERYONE
CAN SUCCEED AT EVERYTHING IN A
COMPETITION.
BY DESIGN, SOMEONE WILL FAIL.
SOMEONE WILL LOSE.
>> IT PISSES ME OFF BUT AT THE
SAME TIME LOGICALLY I
UNDERSTAND.
>> Jeff: TANDANG, NICE JOB.
COME GET YOUR REWARD AND
IMMUNITY.
>> YEAH!
(APPLAUSE)
>> LOOK AT ALL THESE SPICES,
ABI, YOU'RE GONNA GO CRAZY.
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT'S AMAZING.
>> Jeff: KALABAW, NICE JOB,
COME ON OVER.
>> WE'RE GONNA TRADE THE FOOD
FOR THE TARP.
>> REALLY?
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KALABAW
TAKING THE TARP AND IMMUNITY,
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
>> PEACE OUT, GUYS.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, DENICE,
MALCOLM, YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
YOU'RE THE ONLY TRIBE TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU'RE GOING
AGAIN TONIGHT.
ONE OF THE THREE OF YOU WILL BE
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
MY LOWEST LOW WAS AFTER THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
MY DOG DIED A FEW YEARS AGO THAT
I HAD ALL MY LIFE AND I DIDN'T
CRY.
I WAS ABOUT READY TO CRY AFTER
THAT CHALLENGE BECAUSE IT HURT
THAT MUCH.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S DISBELIEF, FRUSTRATION,
SADNESS, ALL THOSE THINGS
BECAUSE TONIGHT WE HAVE TO VOTE
ONE OF THE THREE OF US OUT.
IT COULD BE ME.
>> VOTE DENICE OUT, THAT'S IT.
GOT TO KEEP THE TWO ATHLETES.
>> EXACTLY.
>> YOU KNOW, ME AND DENICE HAVE
BEEN STRATEGICALLY ALIGNED SINCE
DAY ONE BUT I'M HAVING TO MAKE
DECISIONS ON DAY 9 THAT I DIDN'T
CONSIDER HAVING TO MAKE UNTIL
DAY 20 OR SO.
I'D LIKE TO THINK THAT RUSSELL
BELIEVES THAT I'M GOING WITH HIM
TO VOTE OUT DENICE AND KEEP OUR
MATCHUP STRONG GOING FORWARD AND
I'D LIKE FOR DENICE TO BELIEVE
THAT I'M WITH HER AND THAT WE'RE
GOING TO VOTE OUT RUSS LIKE
WE'VE BEEN PLANNING FOR A WEEK
NOW.
>> I'VE GOT MY ALLIANCE THAT'S
WITH MALCOLM AND I HOPE IT'S
STRONG.
FOR ME IT'S STRONG.
BUT IF RUSSELL HAS THE IMMUNITY
IDOL IT'S NOT GOOD.
AND, YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT TO
HAVE TO DRAW ROCKS, I DON'T WANT
TO HAVE TO REVOTE.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO GO
THERE.
SO RIGHT NOW WE'RE TRYING TO GET
RUSSELL TO THING THAT HE'S THE
SWING.
OR TO THINK THAT HE'S COMFORT
SOBL THAT IF HE DOES HAVE AN
IMMUNITY IDOL HE DOESN'T PLAY
IT.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> THIS JUST REALLY SUCKS.
THIS JUST ISN'T RIGHT.
I DON'T GO INTO ANYTHING
EXPECTING LESS THAN THE BEST AND
WHEN I LOSE I'M PISSED.
BUT I'LL GET OVER IT.
I JUST -- I DON'T KNOW ANY OTHER
WAY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW ELSE PEOPLE
APPROACH LIFE.
>> IS THAT HOW YOU'VE ALWAYS
BEEN?
IS THAT HOW YOU'VE ALWAYS
HANDLED --
>> YOU KNOW, IT JUST GOT TO -- I
GOT JUMPED BY TWO KIDS.
I WAS PROBABLY ABOUT EIGHT.
I WAS WALKING HOME FROM SCHOOL
AND, YOU KNOW, I GOT BEAT UP,
BUT BEAT UP AS LITTLE KIDS GET
BEAT UP.
IT WASN'T LIKE A GROWN MAN
BUTT-WHOOPING WHERE YOU'RE IN
THE HOSPITAL.
AND I CAN REMEMBER FOR A LONG
TIME AFTER THAT I WOULD GO TO
SCHOOL AND I WAS SCARED BECAUSE
I WOULD SEE THEM AND THEY WOULD
TEASE AND ALL THAT KIND OF
STUFF.
SO LONG STORY SHORT I CATCH ONE
OF THEM AND WITHOUT EVEN
THINKING I JUST PUNCHED HIM
RIGHT IN HIS FACE AND HE STARTED
CRYING.
AND THERE WAS SOMETHING ABOUT
THAT.
LIKE, NOT THE -- BECAUSE I DON'T
CONDONE VIOLENCE.
BUT IT WAS SOMETHING ABOUT JUST
NOT BEING IN FEAR.
I THINK JUST FROM THAT DAY IT
WAS JUST LIKE I'M NOT GONNA
COWER IN THE FACE OF ANYTHING.
>> I SEE.
SO YOU'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHY WE'RE IN THIS.
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT I DON'T KNOW --
>> THE FIRST THING I'M TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT IF I'M GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> WELL, THAT'S WHAT I -- I
DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR THOUGHTS
ARE BUT LOOK, I LIKE MALCOLM BUT
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY LONG TERM,
ONCE IT'S THERE, ONCE YOU HERE
IN WITH ANOTHER TRIBE PHYSICALLY
--
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER, IT'S ABOUT
SOCIAL AT THAT POINT.
>> EXACTLY.
SOCIALLY HE'S A BIG THREAT.
PHYSICALLY THE WAY HE'S GONNA
PERFORM.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR
THOUGHTS ARE.
>> WELL, I TELL YOU WHAT, IF YOU
VOTE THAT WAY --
>> I MEAN, THAT'S JUST A
THOUGHT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU'RE --
>> SEE, I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS
UP WITH YOU AND MALCOLM.
I HAD ALWAYS ASSUMED THERE WAS
AN ALLIANCE --
>> YOU HAVE TO WEIGH IT OUT
EVERY TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> AND KIND OF GO, WELL, WHAT'S
--
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I'M JUST GLAD TO KNOW
THAT I AT LEAST HAVE A CHANCE.
I THOUGHT I WAS GONE.
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU --
>> I ASSUME I'M GONE.
WE'RE ALL VULNERABLE TONIGHT.
I ASSUME OKAY, WELL --.
>> WELL, DENICE FINALLY HAS KIND
OF SAID SOMETHING TO ME ABOUT
WANTING TO VOTE MALCOLM.
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE, WHAT IF IT
-- WHAT IF IT REALLY IS MALCOLM
WANTING TO VOTE DENICE AND
DENICE WANTING TO VOTE MALCOLM
AND I'M IN THIS PIVOTAL
POSITION.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
>> OH, YOU'RE IS FULL OF MOOD.
YOU WANT KNOW DIG IT?
>> YEAH.
TONIGHT WITH ONLY THREE PEOPLE
AND EVERYONE TELLING EVERYONE
ELSE IT'S THE OTHER PERSON THIS
COULD GO ANY WAY, REALLY.
AND I LIKE TO THINK I'M SITTING
IN THE CONTROLLING SEAT.
>> NO CHANCE WE'RE BEING DRY
TONIGHT.
>> DENICE WALKS UP TO ME, I SAY
"YEAH, WE'RE GETTING RID OF
RUSS."
RUSS WALKED UNTO ME "YEAH, WE'RE
GETTING RID OF DENICE."
RUSS PROBABLY WALKS UP TO DENICE
AND DENICE SAYS "LET'S GET RID
OF MALCOLM.
WE HAVE THE BEST BOND."
IT'S TERRIFYING.
>> YES I'M A MIDWESTERNER, YES I
HAVE FAITH IN HUMAN BEINGS, I
HAVE TO, THAT'S WHAT I HANG ON
TO.
IF I GET BAMBOOZLED TONIGHT IT'S
NOT GOING TO SHAKE MY FAITH THAT
THESE ARE TWO GOOD GUYS.
IT WILL TELL ME THAT, YOU KNOW,
I SCREWED UP AND THEY PLAYED THE
GAME BETTER THAN ME.
>> Jeff: WOW, DENICE, CRAZY,
RIGHT?
>> CRAZY.
THAT DOESN'T EVEN HARDLY EXPLAIN
IT.
ABSOLUTELY NUTS.
>> Jeff: SO, MALCOLM, TODAY AT
CAMP MUST HAVE BEEN INTERESTING
BECAUSE IT WOULD BE A SAFE
ASSUMPTION TO THINK IF PLAYER
ONE SAYS TO PLAYER TWO WHO IS
IT, THEY'RE GOING TO SAY PLAYER
THREE.
>> THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
JUST BECAUSE WE'RE ALL SAYING
THE SAME THING TO EVERYONE.
YOU'RE NOT PLAYING THE GAME IF
YOU'RE NOT SAYING SOMETHING
DIFFERENT TO EVERYBODY RIGHT NOW
.
>> DENICE, YOU FEEL THE SAME
WAY?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
EACH ONE OF US, OUR BAGS ARE
FULL.
IT'S A HELPLESS FEELING.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE CHALLENGE TODAY.
SPECIFICALLY WHEN IT WAS OVER.
ONE OF THE THINGS YOU SAID WAS--
AND I'M PARAPHRASING-- IF I DO
MY BEST I SHOULD WIN.
>> IT'S A MIND-SET, JEFF, AND I
TALKED TO DENICE A LITTLE BIT
TODAY BECAUSE SHE'S A THERAPIST
TO TAKE THE TEMPERATURE OF MY
PERSPECTIVE ON THIS ATTITUDE OF
EXCELLENCE AND YOU KNOW WHERE I
CAME UP?
THERE IS NOTHING WRONG WITH ME
EXPECTING EXCELLENCE FOR MYSELF
EVERY TIME NO MATTER WHAT IT IS
THAT I'M DOING.
SO I'M COMFORTABLE WITH THAT.
IF IT'S A FATAL FLAW, I HAVE TO
ACCEPT IT.
>> Jeff: WHO PUT MALCOLM IN
THE SPOT AT THE END OF THE
CHALLENGE, THE GO-TO GUY.
>> I THREW MY HAND UP, CALLED
FOR THE BALL AND DIDN'T GET THE
JOB DONE AND TAKING ALL THE HEAT
FOR THAT.
FOR THE FIRST FEW CHALLENGES,
YOU KNOW, I THINK WE ALL TO AN
EXTENT FELT WE WERE BEING LET
DOWN BY EVERYBODY ELSE.
AND I TELL YOU WHEN YOU'RE THE
ONE WHO LETS PEOPLE DOWN IT
STINGS DOUBLE.
THAT'S TOTALLY ON ME TODAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
DOWN TO IT.
DENICE, WHY KEEP YOU TONIGHT?
>> I THINK IN TERMS OF WHEREVER
THIS GOES I'LL CONTINUE TO BE A
STRONG PHYSICAL PLAYER.
GOT A STRONG SOCIAL GAME TO HELP
MAKE ALLIANCES GOING OVER
WHEREVER WE END UP.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, WHY KEEP YOU
TONIGHT?
>> WE CAN'T WAIT FOR A TWIST OR
A MERGE OR ANYTHING.
WE HAVE TO WIN SOMETHING AT SOME
POINT AND, YOU KNOW, NO OFFENSE
TO RUSS BUT I GOT 20 YEARS ON
THE GUY.
HE'S STALE HOSS, BUT I GOT PEP
IN MY STEP.
NO E FENCE TO DENICE, SHE'S AN
OX OF A WOMAN, I DROP A FOOT ON
HER VERTICALLY.
I DROPPED THE BALL TODAY BUT I
THINK WE'RE THE BIGGEST PHYSICAL
ASSET WE HAVE.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, WHY SHOULD
MALCOLM NOT BE HERE TONIGHT?
>> BECAUSE HE IS SUCH A YOUNG
STUD.
HE'S A THREAT.
NOT TO SAY THAT I'M NOT.
BUT WHEN I GROW UP I WANT TO BE
LIKE MALCOLM.
THIS GUY IS INCREDIBLE.
>> Jeff: SO YOUR ARGUMENT TO
DENICE TO KEEP YOU IS WHAT?
>> OKAY, LOOK, WE HAVE TO
COMPETE.
I CAN COMPETE.
CAN'T COMPETE LIKE MALCOLM.
BUT I'M NO SLOUCH.
AND THERE'S STILL GOING TO BE
SOMETHING ON THE SOCIAL END
GOING FORWARD.
AND I CAN DO THAT, TOO, BASED ON
WHAT I KNOW EXPERIENTIALLY WHAT
NEEDS TO HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: SO FEW F YOU TWO STAY
TOGETHER YOU COULD MAYBE
SURVIVE?
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, TELL ME WHY
IT MAKES SENSE TO GET RID OF
DENICE TONIGHT.
>> SHE'S A STEP ABOVE ALL OF US
SOCIALLY.
I DON'T THINK ANYTHING ANYBODY
CAN SAY A SINGLE NEGATIVE THING
ABOUT DENICE AT THIS POINT.
>> SHE GETS IN FRONT OF A JURY
THEY WILL STAND UP, THEY WILL
SAY "YOU GUYS SUCK, YOU SUCK,
SHE WINS."
>> Jeff: (LAUGHS)
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'RE GREAT,
YOU'RE CUTE, YOU LOOK FUNNY.
>> YOU'RE ENTHUSIASTIC.
OH BUT THERE'S DENICE.
>> CAN I WRITE YOU MY OWN CHECK
ALONG WITH THE CHECK YOU GET
FROM "SURVIVOR" TO HELP WITH THE
TAXES?
(LAUGHTER)
>> Jeff: SO MALCOLM, WHAT DO
YOU THINK IS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT?
>> I THINK THAT THE TWO GOING
FORWARD ARE GOING TO BE THE TWO
THAT HAVE THE BEST CHANCE
TOGETHER TO GO DEEP IN THIS
GAME.
>> Jeff: AND WITH THAT IT IS
TIME TO VOTE.
RUSSELL, YOU'RE UP.
>> I'M ONLY MAKING THIS VOTE
BECAUSE YOU'RE JUST GONNA BE TOO
BIG A THREAT GOING FORWARD, BUT
YOU ARE A GREAT KID.
>> SORRY, BROTHER.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
(THUNDERCLAPS)
>> Jeff: OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES
ARE READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, RUSS.
MALCOLM.
ONE VOTE MALCOLM; ONE VOTE RUSS.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES" --
>> OH!
>> Jeff: RUSS.
BRING YOUR TORCH.
RUSS, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> WELL, THERE'S NOT MUCH TO
SAY.
YOU'RE DOWN TO TWO, YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE GOT TO DO: KEEP
FIGHTING.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: TEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
WITH MATSING DOWN TO ONLY TWO
MEMBERS --
>> THERE'S TWO OF US AGAINST TWO
TRIBES OF SIX.
>> Jeff: THE IDOL IS THEIR
ONLY HOPE.
>> THIS MIGHT BE MY LAST CHANCE.
I FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT.
>> Jeff: FOR KALABAW
EVERYTHING IS ABOUT TO CHANGE.
>> THE ONLY TIME MEDICAL PULLS
ANYBODY FROM THIS GAME IS WHEN
THEIR LIFE IS IN DANGER.
WOW.
>> RIGHT NOW IT'S JUST UTTER
SHOCK.
I WAS COMPLETELY BLINDSIDED.
IT'S BEEN A ROUGH TEN DAYS WET
WISE, DEALING WITH MY TRIBE THIS
WHICH WAS DEFINITELY
DYSFUNCTIONAL IN SO MANY WAYS
AND THIS WAS JUST THE STRAW THAT
BREAKS THE CAMEL'S BACK AND IT'S
OBVIOUS ME AND "SURVIVOR" DON'T
GET ALONG SO I THINK I'M DONE
WITH THIS.