>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
AFTER 13 DAYS IN A BATTLE
BETWEEN THREE TRIBES-- MATSING
LOSES AGAIN!
TANDANG AND KALABAW HAD YET TO
LOSE WHILE MATSING HAD YET TO
WIN.
IT WAS DOWN TO MALCOLM AND
DENICE.
>> WE'RE ABOUT AS DOWN AND OUT
AS YOU CAN GET AT THIS POINT.
>> BUT WHEN YOU'RE DEAD IN THE
WATER, AN IDOL CAN BREATHE NEW
LIFE.
>> THIS GIVES ME A HUGE AMOUNT
OF POWER IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: AT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE MALCOLM, DENICE, DROP
YOUR BUFFS.
MATSING WAS NO MORE.
MALCOLM AND DENICE STARTED NEW
CHAPTERS ON SEPARATE TRIBES.
WE HAVE TWO TRIBES NOW.
TANDANG, MALCOLM FELT RIGHT AT
HOME, GAINING PETE'S TRUST.
>> WE HAVE THE IDOL.
I FEEL LIKE I GOT MY SWAG BACK.
>> PUTTING MIKE AND R.C. FURTHER
ON THE OUTS.
>> I DIDN'T WORK TO LET THEM
WALK ALL OVER ME.
I'M GOING TO FIGHT.
>> Jeff: AT KALABAW, THERE
WERE TWO ALLIANCES HEADING IN
OPPOSITE DIRECTIONS.
THE MEN'S ALLIANCE HAD PENNER'S
IDOL.
>> THE IDOL IS RIGHT UNDER YOUR
NOSE.
>> Jeff: AND GREW STRONGER
WHEN THEY RECRUITED DENICE.
>> IF YOU'RE WITH US, YOU'RE THE
FOURTH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
EVERY STEP IS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
TURN THINGS AROUND.
STPHAOUL WHILE THE WOMEN'S
ALLIANCE WAS HIT HARD.
>> I CAN'T BE OUT HERE!
>> Jeff: WHEN DANA PULLED
HERSELF FROM THE GAME.
>> MY BEST ALLY GOT TAKEN AWAY,
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO TO
SURVIVE?
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, KATIE STRUGGLED.
TANDANG WINS IMMUNITY!
COSTING KALABAW THE VICTORY.
BACK IN CAMP, IN THE FACE OF
DIMINISHING NUMBERS, STRENGTH
WAS VITAL AND KATIE WAS AN EASY
TARGET.
>> I WAS BAD.
>> Jeff: BUT WHEN DAWSON
MESSED WITH THE BULL --
>> THE BRAVES ARE THE BEST TEAM.
>> Jeff: SHE GOT THE HORNS.
I USED TO BE A BALL PLAYER.
IF BUT A SON KNOWS, BEST
SCENARIO MIGHT BE TO VOTE HER
OUT.
>> Jeff: FIFTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF "SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES,"
DAWSON.
12 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
>> I AM TOTALLY WORRIED BECAUSE
I DON'T HAVE MY GIRLS ANYMORE TO
HELP ME OUT.
SO I'M AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
TOTEM POLYPOLE NOW AND I HAVE TO
FIND MY WAY OUT OF IT.
STRENGTH IS GOING TO DRIVE THIS
AND I'M LOOKING LIKE THE WEAKEST
LENGTH SO I'VE GOT TO WORK MY
MAGIC AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> DID YOU KNOWS HE BROUGHT HIS
BAG WITH HIM TO TRIBAL?
HE KNEW HE WASN'T GOING HOME BUT
HE HAD IT ON HIM JUST IN CASE.
>> I JUST DO.
I THINK HE'S GOT IT.
>> I THINK SO, TOO.
>> I THINK HE'S GOT IT.
>> IN THIS GAME IT'S EVERY
SINGLE MAN FOR HIMSELF AND IF
THAT MEANS PLANTING SEEDS IN N
PEOPLE'S HEADS, I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO DO WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
>> OKAY, WE TAKE OUT STRENGTH
NOW OR STRENGTH AFTER THE MERGE?
>> THERE'S NO GUARANTEE AFTER
THE MERGE.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE.
SO I THINK WE HAVE TO GET RID OF
PENNER.
IT'S A NO-BRAINER.
IF I CAN GET RID OF JONATHAN,
THAT'S GOING TO KEEP ME HERE AT
LEAST THROUGH THE MERGE AND I
INTEND ON MAKING THAT HAPPEN.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
JUST TO GET IT GOING BECAUSE WE
SHOULD MAKE BREAKFAST.
>> WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF RICE
LEFT.
>> WE DON'T?
>> NO.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU ALL BEEN DOING?
>> EATING RAW RICE.
(LAUGHS)
>> WE HAVEN'T REALLY HAD MUCH TO
EAT, ESPECIALLY SINCE MIKE
DECIDED TO DEPLETE ALL OF OUR
RICE RESOURCE BY EATING IT DRY.
>> THIS IS THE WAY CHICKENS EAT
EVERYDAY, RIGHT?
>> HE THINKS IT COOKS IN YOUR
BODY BECAUSE IT'S PRETTY CLOSE
TO 100 DEGREES.
SO MIKE MAKES HORRIBLE
DECISIONS.
HE'S THE MOST USELESS PLAYER
EVER RETURNED TO "SURVIVOR" AND
HE NEEDS TO GO HOME.
>> I DON'T WANT TO MAKE
BREAKFAST.
I WANT TO BE CAREFUL.
>> NOTHING FOR THE CHALLENGE?
>> UNLESS YOU'D RATHER BE HUNGRY
FOR THE REST OF YOUR TIME HERE.
>> I'M JUST SAYING EVEN IF WE
MADE ONE CUP AND SPLIT IT
BETWEEN EVERYBODY FOR BREAKFAST?
LIKE, JUST SOMETHING IN OUR
STOMACHS?
>> YES, EVEN, EVEN.
>> AS A RETURNING PLAYER, I JUST
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MIKE IS LITERALLY ATE US OUT OF
HOUSE AND HOME.
WE HAVE NO FOOD BECAUSE OF MIKE.
I CONSIDER US TANDANG PLUS ONE.
AND MIKE'S THE ONE.
AND RIGHT NOW WITH US GETTING
MALCOLM, MIKE HAS BECOME
EXPENDABLE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
TANDANG GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW KALABAW TRIBE.
DAWSON VOTES OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ON MY GO, THREE
MEMBERS FROM EACH TRIBE WILL
RACE OUT TO THE LARGE WICKER
BALL.
YOU WILL WORK TOGETHER TO PUSH
THAT BALL THROUGH YOUR GOAL
WHILE THE OTHER TRIBE IS DOING
EVERYTHING THEY CAN TO STOP YOU.
EACH TIME YOU GET THE BALL
THROUGH YOUR GOAL YOU SCORE A
POINT FOR YOUR TRIBE.
FIRST TRIBE TO THREE WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: AFTER 13 DAYS, YOU
NEED SOME FOOD.
THE WINNING TRIBE WILL BE TAKEN
TO A DRY HUT WHERE YOU WILL HAVE
SANDWICHES, SOUP, POTATO CHIPS,
BROWNIES.
>> OH, MY WORD!
>> Jeff: WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: TANDANG, YOU HAVE TWO
EXTRA MEMBERS THAT ARE GOING TO
SIT OUT ONE MAN AND ONE WOMAN.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
R.C. AND ARTIS, TAKE A SEAT ON
THE BENCH.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
FIRST ROUND, LISA, PETE AND
SKUPIN FOR TANDANG GOING UP
AGAINST PENNER, CARTER AND
DENICE FROM KALABAW.
HERE WE GO!
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS A RACE TO GET THAT BALL
FIRST SKUPIN AND CARTER GET
THERE AT THE SAME TIME.
>> DIG DEEP!
>> TAKE HIM DOWN, SKAOUP!
>> HE TAKES DOWN CARTER HARD.
TAKING ON DENICE BUT HAVING NO
LUCK.
IT'S GETTING PHYSICAL RIGHT OFF
THE BAT.
>> COME ON, PETE!
>> Jeff: BIG REWARD ON THE
LINE.
KALABAW FEEDS A WIN.
THEY WANT THE FOOD AND THEY WANT
TO REMIND TANDANG THEY ARE STILL
IN THIS GAME.
>> THERE YOU GO, LISA!
>> LISA FINALLY GETS DENICE DOWN
WITH A MIKE TAKEDOWN.
PETE GOING HARD AFTER CARTER.
THE PROBLEM IS NOBODY CAN MOVE
THE BALL EITHER WAY.
>> HANG ON TO THAT BALL, DENICE.
>> HOLD ON!
>> DENICE AND LISA GETTING
SQUISHED BY THIS BALL.
PETE TAKES DOWN CARTER AGAIN.
SKUPIN GOING AFTER PENNER NOW!
>> LISA, GET UP!
DENICE IS NOW WORKING IT FOR
KALABAW!
CARTER TAKES DOWN PETE.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING IN HIM.
KALABAW GAINING SLOWLY.
GETTING CLOSER TO THAT GOAL.
>> SPIN IT TOWARDS US.
GO!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN WITH A BIG
TAKEDOWN OF CART ERE OPENING THE
DOOR FOR PETE.
PENNER ISN'T HAVING IT.
LISA HAS DENICE DOWN AND SHE CAN
NOT GET UP.
PETE IS PUSHING AND PENNER IS
PULLING.
BIG BATTLE GOING.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR" CHALLENGE
OLD SCHOOL RIGHT HERE.
DOWN AND DIRTY IN THE MUD!
>> PENNER'S GETTING FRISKY!
>> SORRY, BUTT DI.
>> Jeff: TO BE CLEAR, PENNER'S
DOING NOTHING ILLEGAL.
HE HAS HIS HAND BETWEEN SKUPIN'S
LEG.
VERY INTIMATE WAY TO PLAY THIS
GAME BUT TOTALLY LEGAL.
>> GOOD JOB, LISA.
SKUPIN NOW SITTING ON PENNER.
WE HERE IN A FULL LOCKDOWN.
LISA HAS DENICE, SKUPIN HAS
PENNER.
PETE AND CARTER ARE TIED UP
TOGETHER.
SOMEBODY WILL WEAR DOWN.
>> ENDURANCE IS WHAT'S GOING TO
WIN!
SOMETHING SKUPIN AND I BOTH
HAVE.
WE'RE READY TO SIT HERE ALL
NIGHT IF IT TAKES IT.
I THINK.
>> ABSOLUTELY, MAN.
>> THIS IS LIKE HEAVEN.
>> WELL, YEAH.
IT'S LIKE SOMETHING.
ONE HOUR.
THE BALL HAS NOT MOVED IN A LONG
TIME.
SPEAKS TO HOW EVENLY DIVIDED
THESE TWO TRIBES ARE.
>> CARTER, WHAT YOU GOT, BUD
ECONOMY?
YOU WANT TO TAKE ONE LAST ONE?
>> DUDE, I --
>> PENNER --
>> Jeff: PETE WITH A DIG
TAKEDOWN ON CARTER.
WE'VE GOT SOME MOVEMENT GOING
NOW.
LISA HAS DENICE TIED UP SO IT'S
PENNER AND SKUPIN.
NOTHING HAPPENS.
WE'RE BACK TO ANOTHER SHOWDOWN.
PENNER AND SKUPIN EXHAUSTED.
>> WHAT YOU GUYS WANNA DO?
>> BEAT YOU.
>> LET'S TALK TURKEY.
WE'RE GONNA DO THIS AND WE'RE
GONNA HAVE TO GO AT IT AGAIN.
JEFF, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> TWO-THIRDS OF THE WAY THERE.
>> WE'LL TRADE OUR SANDWICHES --
>> WE'RE TRYING TO GAIN FOOD.
>> WE'LL TRADE YOUR SANDWICHES
FOR WHAT?
>> THE REST OF YOUR RICE.
>> WHOA!
COME ON!
>> YOU CAN CANCEL THAT.
>> WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH THEY
HAVE.
>> WE'RE JUST TALKING.
>> I CONSIDER THAT, SERIOUSLY.
>> BUT I DON'T KNOW, RICE FUELS
US.
>> Jeff: PENNER, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO FOR FOOD AFTER THIS
AFTERNOON.
>> I GOT A BOAT, I GOT A SPEAR,
I GOT A SNORKEL.
>> AND WE GOT PLANS, BIG ONES.
>> GUYS, LET'S TALK ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS COME UP WITH
AN ALTERNATE PLAN FOR THIS AND
EVERYBODY AGREES TO IT, I'M
OPEN.
OTHERWISE THIS GOES AS PLANNED.
GOT TO SCORE THREE.
>> I SAY WE GIVE YOU GUYS THE
RICE, WE TAKE THE SANDWICHES.
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN, THAT'S
LIKE FIVE --
>> ARTIS, WEIGH IN HERE, IT'S
YOUR BIRTHDAY.
>> COME ON, BIRTHDAY BOY.
WE HAVEN'T HEARD ANYTHING.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR WHAT I
GOT TO SAY ABOUT IT.
WHAT I WANT TO DO, I WANT TO
WIN.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP NOTHING.
>.AND YOU CAN KEEP THAT MESS TO
YOURSELF.
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CALM DOWN.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU GUYS, FROM A STRAEPBLG
STRATEGIC STANDPOINT, LET'S TAKE
THEIR FOOD AND GO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S
SETTLE THIS.
HERE'S WHAT'S ON THE TABLE RIGHT
NOW.
KALABAW IS SAYING GIVE US THIS
VICTORY, LET US HAVE THE REWARD
IN EXCHANGE WE WILL GIVE YOU ALL
THE RICE WE HAVE.
>> YUP.
>> I'M WITH THE MAJORITY.
>> CARTER, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> YOU THINK WE CAN CATCH FISH,
I'LL DO IT.
>> WE JUST NEED ENOUGH TIME WITH
THE BOAT AND I'LL CATCH THEM.
>> FINE.
>> ME AND PETE ARE SAYING YES TO
THAT DEAL.
>> I SAY YES.
>> WE KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE OUT
HERE.
>> DO YOU WANT YOU WANT TO DO,
MIKE.
>> WE'RE NOT SAYING ANYTHING,
YOU GUYS DECIDE WHATEVER YOU
WANT TO DO.
>> YES OR NO, TANDANG?
>> I'M FOR IT, MAN.
>> Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE IS
OVER.
REWARD GOES TO KALABAW!
IN EXCHANGE FOR ALL THE RICE
THEY HAVE LEFT AT CAMP.
>> GOOD JOB, TANDANG.
>> Y'ALL ARE JUST NOT SEEING THE
BIG PICTURE.
>> Jeff: I'M PRETTY SURE THIS
IS UNPRECEDENTED.
JEFF, YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE UP
ALL YOUR RICE, WHICH PUTS A HUGE
BURDEN ON THIS TRIBE TO GO OUT
AND FISH IN CONDITIONS THAT HAVE
BEENLESS THAN OPTIMAL.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WORK.
OUR ENERGY, IT'S GOING TO BE
WASTED FISHING AND CLAMMING AND
SCRAPING AND CLAWING FOR FOOD
AND THESE PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
GET THEIR BELLIES FULL OF RICE,
BUT WE HAVE TO FIND SOME OTHER
WAY TO GET FOOD.
>> Jeff: KALABAW, HERE'S
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE HERE, BE
TAKE ON THE A NICE, DRY SPOT.
WASH OFF THEN YOU WILL HAVE A
NICE LUNCH.
HOPEFULLY IT'S WORTH THE DEAL
YOU JUST MADE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT AND
ENJOY.
TANDANG, KALABAW'S RICE WILL BE
DELIVERED TO YOUR TREEMAIL.
I HOPE THE DEAL WAS WORTH IT FOR
YOU GUYS AS WELL.
OTHER THAN THAT, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
>> WHOA!
>> SHOULD WE PICK UP ONE BROWNIE
AND ALL TAKE A BITE OF IT REAL
QUICK?
>> YES, WE SHOULD.
>> YOU PICK IT UP.
>> EVERYONE GETS A BITE OF IT.
>> OH, GOD!
OH!
>> WE ARRIVED AT THE REWARD
COVERED IN MUD, WE CLEANED
OURSELVES UP AND SAT DOWN TO THE
MOST DELICIOUS PICNIC LUNCH I'VE
EVER HAD.
OH, MY LORD, LOOK AT THOSE
SANDWICHES!
>> OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS LIKE AVOCADO, BACON AND
TURKEY.
>> THE REWARD WAS PRETTY INSANE.
THOSE SANDWICHES, THEY WERE ALL
GREAT AND HOPEFULLY THIS WILL
GIVE US SOME KIND OF ADVANTAGE,
SOME KIND OF MOMENTUM.
>> WELL, IT'S INTERESTING, WE
LUCKED OUT, YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHY?
IF THEY'D WON THERE WOULD BE
SEVEN PEOPLE SITTING AT THE SAME
MEAL AS THIS.
FIVE PEOPLE, WE GOT A LOT MORE
FOOD THIS WAY.
THIS WILL TIDE US OVER UNTIL
TOMORROW.
TOMORROW WE'LL FISH, RIGHT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> IT WAS A GREAT MOMENT TO SEE
ALL THAT FOOD ON THE TABLE.
BUT THE FACT THAT WE JUST DON'T
HAVE RICE IS -- IS PROBABLY
GOING TO WEAR ON US IN A COUPLE
DAYS.
>> YOU GUYS, I'M GOING TO BRING
YOU SOMETHING, I'M NOT SURE WHAT
IT'S IN IT BUT IT MAY BE REALLY
COOL.
>> IN THE MIDDLE OF THAT WE
REALIZED OUR TABLE OFF TO THE
SIDE WERE LITTLE ENVELOPES WITH
OUR NAMES ON THEM.
KATIE, DENICE --
>> I KNEW WHAT IT WAS IN THESE
ENVELOPES AND IT WAS OUR LETTERS
FROM HOME.
>> COME ON!
>> OH, NO!
>> THE TRIBE STARTED READING
THEIR LETTERS AND INSTANTLY
PEOPLE STARTED TEARING UP.
WE'RE SO FAR FROM REALITY OUT
HERE THAT WHEN WE GET A GLIMPSE
OF IT JUST HITS IN A PLACE THAT
WE'RE NOT USED TO.
I JUST WANT TO GO HOME NOW.
I'VE GOT A PRETTY BIG FAMILY AT
HOME.
HAVING A WIFE AND KIDS WRITE TO
YOU AFTER SUFFERING THROUGH RAIN
AND NO FOOD AND GETTING BANGED
UP, THAT WAS PRETTY NEAT.
IT'S ALREADY 100 DEGREES IN
TEXAS.
>> COMING TO THIS REWARD, IT'S
MOTIVATIONAL FUEL, IT'S
EMOTIONAL FUEL THAT MAKES ANY
RICE WE GAVE UP TOTALLY WORTH IT
BECAUSE NOW THERE'S DIFFERENT
MOTIVATION TO JUST KEEP GOING.
>> BETTER THAN FOOD.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY
MISSED.
>> WE CAME IN TERMED TO WIN AND
I THINK THIS WAS A WIN.
WE WERE ABLE TO WALK AWAY WITH
THIS VICTORY MEAL AND THESE
BEAUTIFUL LETTERS FROM HOME.
WE'RE GOING TO BE STRONG GOING
INTO THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
WHICH IS REALLY THE IMPORTANT
CHALLENGE.
>> SORRY, ARTIS.
I WANTED TO GIVE YOU A BIRTHDAY
FEAST.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT FEELS BRUTAL THAT KALABAW IS
ENJOYING THE REWARD THAT WE
SHOULD HAVE AND WE'RE BACK HERE
FIGHTING FOR SURVIVAL.
>> WHAT REALLY BOTHERS ME IS WE
HAD A MEMBER OF OUR TRIBE MAKE A
DECISION FOR OUR TRIBE WHO HAS
DONE ABSOLUTELY NOTHING FOR OUR
TRIBE.
AND R.C., YAY, MIKE!
YAY!
I WAS LIKE SHUT UP, IT'S NOT A
GOOD DEAL.
>> HERE'S THE RICE YOU GUYS
WANTED TO FORFEIT FOR, ENJOY.
>> HOW MUCH DO WE HAVE?
>> BASICALLY HOW MUCH WE HAVE
RIGHT NOW.
>> WE DOUBLED OUR RICE.
>> THEY DON'T HAVE ANY.
>> IF THE SUN WOULD COME OUT WE
COULD ACTUALLY COOK SOME OF THAT
RICE.
>> WE'LL BE ABLE TO COOK
TONIGHT.
>> GOOD, THANK YOU.
THAT FEELS GOOD.
WHEN WE GOT BACK, IT WAS WORSE
THAN A LOSS AND IT SHOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN BECAUSE WITH A LOSS
YOU DON'T HAVE ALSO ALL THEIR
RICE.
BUT IT WAS A GIVING UP, A
FORFEIT WHICH WAS LIKE A DOUBLE
LOSS IF YOU CHOOSE TO FOCUS YOUR
ENERGY THAT WAY.
>> I'M AFRAID THIS IS GOING TO
BE ONE OF THE DUMBEST MOMENTS OF
"SURVIVOR."
PEOPLE GO UNTIL THEY AT LEAST
LOSE.
JUST GIVING OUT A PRIZE LIKE
THAT?
NEVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
>> I MEAN THEY DID GIVE US A LOT
MORE THAN WE THINK.
>> AND THEY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
>> THEY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
>> YEAH, THEY DO.
THEY HAVE BEER, THEY HAVE --
>> I'M TRYING TO PUT A POSITIVE
SPIN ON IT.
>> SANDWICHES, BROWNIES, SOUP.
>> WE GAVE UP A REWARD.
WE DIDN'T FIGHT FOR IT.
AND I DOUBT KALABAW WOULD GIVE
US ALL OF THEIR RICE WITHOUT
HAVING A PLAN "B."
THEY HAVE A BOAT AND THEY HAVE A
SPEAR, THEY CAN GO OUT THERE
FISHING.
THEY'RE NOT STUPID.
KALABAW TOTALLY USED PSYCHOLOGY
AND IT WORKED.
SO WE HAVE ONE MORE DAY OUT OF
RICE OUT OF THEIRS AND HOW MUCH
DO WE HAVE OUT OF OURS?
>> ONE.
>> SO WE HAVE TWO DAYS LEFT.
>> WELL, IF WE SEPARATE IT
OTHERWISE THIS IS A BIG POT
HAVE TWO MORE DAYS LEFT OF RICE.
NOT A WEEK LIKE WE THOUGHT.
>> WE HAVE TO START EATING
SMALLER.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY
HERE.
BUT EVERYBODY'S HUNGRY.
FREAKING STUPID.
>> WE NEVER COME BACK FROM A
CHALLENGE AND WE'RE HAPPY BUT IN
"SURVIVOR" WORLD YOU SORT OF
HAVE TO SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE AND
DO THINGS YOU DON'T NORMALLY DO.
BUT THIS IS JUST NASTY.
>> ARTIS WAS CURSING UP A STORM
THROUGH THE COMPETITION.
AND CURSING AT YOU.
>> WHAT DID I DO?
>> NOTHING.
I DON'T THINK YOU DID ANYTHING.
HE WAS JUST REALLY UPSET.
SEEMS LIKE HE WANTED NO PART OF
IT.
>> THEN WHY DID HE AGREE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THERE WAS NO WINNING THAT
CHALLENGE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
>> ARTIS, HE'S LIKE A TEENAGE
GIRL.
HE'LL WHISPER TO EVERYBODY ELSE
BUT HE WON'T CONFRONT ME.
BUT I DIDN'T MAKE THIS DECISION.
>> NO, YOU ASKED EVERY SINGLE
PERSON WHAT THEIR DECISION WAS.
>> AND THEY SAID YES.
>> YEAH!
>> SO NOW THEY'RE GOING TO BLAME
IT ON US.
>> AND THEN ABI IS OBVIOUSLY
DOING HER ABI THING.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'VE EVER MET
ANYBODY THAT NEGATIVE.
>> ARTIS, PETE AND ABI-MARIA ARE
VERY NASTY AND ANGRY AND THEY'RE
CRUEL.
BUT THEY HAD THE UPPER HAND SO
MY STRATEGY IS TO LET ABI-MARIA
BLOW UP CONSTANTLY-- (LAUGHS)
-- AND ME JUST SLIDE UNDER THE
RADAR.
BUT SHE'S LIKE THIS BRAZILIAN
BOMB THAT'S ABOUT TO BLOW UP AT
ANY SECOND.
TODAY.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
THIS IS THE SUBRHYS WE'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
>> STINGRAY'S BACK, WHERE'S THE
SLING?
>> RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU, MAN.
RIGHT THERE.
>> HE JUST FLEW AWAY.
>> SHOOT.
>> HE'LL BE BACK.
IT'S OKAY.
>> AT THE REWARD CHALLENGE WE
MADE A DEAL WITH THE YELLOW
TRIBE THAT WE'D GIVE THEM THE
REST OF OUR RICE AND WE'D TAKE
THE REWARD.
IN ALL HONESTY, I DIDN'T LIKE
THE DEAL WE CAME UP WITH BECAUSE
WE HAD NO GUARANTEE OF FOOD AT
THE MOMENT.
>> IT'S ALL GONNA BE GOOD.
>> I'M GONNA CATCH SOME FISH.
>> JONATHAN'S VERY CONFIDENT
THAT WE CAN GET FISH BUT TO ME
IT WAS A PRETTY RISKY DEAL.
IT JUST REALLY MAKES ME NERVOUS.
>> I'M HUNGRY.
>> I DON'T KNOW MANY MY BODY CAN
LAST THROUGH THIS GAME.
>> REALLY.
>> YEAH.
IF WE HAVE TO PLAY THE STARVING
GAME, LIKE WHO CAN JUST
OUTSTARVE SOMEONE I'M GONNA
LOSE.
>> OH, I'LL LOSE, TOO, DON'T
WORRY.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO GUT THE FISH.
>> THAT'S IT?
>> THAT'S IT.
>> JONATHAN COMES BACK AND I'M,
LIKE, DID YOU CATCH ANYTHING?
AND HE'S LIKE, YEAH, YEAH, WE
CAUGHT TWO FISH, THEY'RE RIGHT
THERE.
GOOD LORD.
>> SUSHI'S GREAT.
YOU LIKE SUSHI, DON'T YOU?
THIS IS PURE PROTEIN.
>> HOW ARE FIVE PEOPLE GOING TO
EAT THESE?
>> IT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
IT CAN'T BE FRESHER.
>> THAT RICE GAVE YOU IMMEDIATE
ENERGY, BUT NOW IT'S GONE AND
JONATHAN'S TRYING TO STAY
POSITIVE "OH, WE GOT PLENTY OF
FOOD, WE GOT PLENTY OF FOOD!"
NO, WE DON'T.
HOW CAN YOU POSSIBLY DO GOOD IN
A CHALLENGE WITH -- LIKE, YOU
NEED FUEL.
>> IF WE DON'T HAVE A MERGE
WITHIN A WEEK WE MAY BE IN
TROUBLE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO LAY
DOWN ALL DAY.
>> CARTER'S GETTING A LITTLE
FRUSTRATED.
I PROMISED HIM THERE'D BE FOOD
AND WE'D EAT AND NOW HE'S JUST
FEELING LIKE WE'LL NEVER FIND
ANY FOOD AND I'M GOING TO STARVE
AND I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT FULL BUT I'M NOT HUNGRY
AFTER THAT MEAL.
HOW DO YOU GUYS FEEL?
I KNOW YOU'RE HUNGRY, CARTER.
>> I WISH WE WOULD HAVE GOT THAT
STINGRAY.
>> THE DEPRIVATION JUST DOESN'T
AFFECT ME THE WAY IT AFFECTS
SOME OF THESE YOUNGER PLAYERS.
BUT THE TRUTH IS, TODAY WE HAVE
AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE AND IT'S
CRUCIALLY IMPORTANT THAT WE WIN
TODAY.
WE HAVE TO GET SOME MOMENTUM
BACK.
THE NUMBERS ARE TIPPING BADLY
AND IF WE CONTINUE TO LOSE, WE
ARE TRULY SCREWED.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
ABI-MARIA, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE ONE TRIBE
MEMBER WILL LAUNCH BALLS OUT
INTO THE FIELD WHILE THE OTHER
TRIBE MEMBERS ATTEMPT TO CATCH
THE BALL.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHICH COLOR.
IF YOU CATCH A BALL YOU SCORE A
POINT FOR YOUR TRIBE.
FIRST TRIBE TO STORE FIVE WINS
IMMUNITY, A T SAFE FROM THE
VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
TANDANG, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
MEMBERS.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SIT OUT
THIS TIME?
IT HAS TO BE A MAN AND A WOMAN.
>> ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS.
ONE, TWO, THREE, SHOOT.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN GOING TO SIT
THIS ONE OUT ALONG WITH WHO?
ABI, YOU'RE SITTING OUT AGAIN.
THAT IS, WHAT, TWO OUT OF EIGHT
CHALLENGES YOU'VE PARTICIPATED
IN?
>> WELL, IT WASN'T MY CHOICE.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN AND ABI, TAKE
A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR MATCHUPS.
LISA GOING TO BE LAUNCHING BALLS
FOR TANDANG, DENICE WILL BE THE
LAUNCHER FOR KALABAW.
STARTING OUT ON ONE POLE ARTIS
AND PENNER.
WE'VE GOT MALCOLM AND CARTER
GOING AT IT, JEFF AGAINST PETE
AND R.C. AGAINST KATIE.
ONCE THE BALLS ARE LAUNCHED THEY
ARE UP FOR GRABS.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
RELEASE.
TWO BALLS IN THE AIR QUICKLY.
PENNER SCORES FOR KALABAW!
>> WHOO!
>> Jeff: KALABAW ON THE BOARD
1-ZIP KALABAW LEADS.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BALL'S IN THE AIR AGAIN.
PETE CATCHES FOR TANDANG!
R.C. CATCHES FOR TANDANG!
TWO POINTS ON THAT ROUND FOR
TANDANG!
TANDANG NOW LEADS 2-1.
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO, SURVIVORS
READY?
RELEASE.
KATIE CAN'T CONNECT.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: CARTER STRUGGLING
EARLY.
KALABAW NEEDS TO PICK IT UP.
NO SCORE THAT ROUND.
RELEASE.
DENICE GOES SHORT.
PENNER CAN'T GET THERE.
LISA LAUNCHES.
JEFF WITH A CATCH FOR KALABAW!
WE ARE TIED 2-2.
>> COME ON, KALABAW!
>> Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> LONG, LONG, LONG!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, JEFF GOES
HIGH AND SCORES FOR KALABAW!
>> NICE CATCH, BUDDY!
>> Jeff: KALABAW LEADS 3-2.
GOOD MATCH GOING HERE.
VERY EVEN.
SURVIVORS READY?
KATIE, HAND ON THE POLE.
>> OH, SORRY.
>> Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> LONG, LONG!
>> Jeff: JEFF WITH ANOTHER
CATCH FOR KALABAW.
LISA GOES DEEP.
R.C. AND KATIE CAN'T CONNECT.
KATIE COMPLETELY INEFFECTIVE IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
KALABAW LEADS 4-2.
PLAYING TO FIVE, THIS COULD BE
IT.
TANDANG TRYING TO STAY ALIVE.
>> GO FOR MALCOLM.
GO RIGHT FOR MALCOLM.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
RELEASE.
DENICE GOES FIRST THEN LISA.
RIGHT TO MALCOLM.
>> Jeff: WHOO!
MALCOLM SCORES FOR TANDANG!
KALABAW LEADS 4-3.
KALABAW CAN STILL WIN IT RIGHT
HERE.
>> GO LISA!
>> Jeff: JEFF CAN WIN IT.
JEFF HAD IT KNOCKED OUT OF HIS
HANDS BY PETE!
MALCOLM WITH AN AMAZING GRAB FOR
TANDANG!
MALCOLM IS ON A TEAR FOR TANDANG
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
HE IS EATING CARTER'S LUNCH.
>> GO, MALCOLM!
>> FIGHT!
>> OKAY, CARTER, IF YOU WANT HIM
OR YOU WANT TO LET JEFF TAKE
HIM?
>> JEFF, YOU WANT THIS?
>> I'M IN.
>> Jeff: CARTER NOW GOING TO
SWITCH OUT.
JEFF GOING TO SEE IF HE CAN TAKE
MALCOLM DOWN.
MALCOLM HAS BEEN ON FIRE.
WE ARE TIED 4-4.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
DENICE GOES SHORT PENNER WAS
RIGHT THERE, COULDN'T CONNECT.
LISA LAUNCHES.
MALCOLM SCORES EVEN ON JEFF!
TANDANG WINS IMMUNITY!
>> YES, YES, YES!
>> GREAT JOB!
GREAT!
>> Jeff: TANDANG,
CONGRATULATIONS.
PROBABLY MALCOLM WHO SHOULD BE
HOLDING THAT.
>> NO, NO, NO!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, HUGE EFFORT.
TANDANG, ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF, NO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, NOBODY GOING
HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> THANKS.
>> Jeff: KALABAW, TONIGHT
SOMEBODY WILL BE GOING HOME.
JEFF, KATIE, PENNER, CARTER,
DENICE.
AFTER 16 DAYS, SOMEBODY'S SHOT
AT THE MILLION DOLLARS WILL COME
TO AN END.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
THEY TOTALLY KNEW WHERE TO PUT
THE BALL SO THAT NOBODY BUT HIM
COULD GET THERE.
>> WE SHOULD HAVE WRAPPED HIM
UP.
WE SHOULD HAVE JUST JUMPED ON
HIM.
WE WERE OVERMATCHED.
>> AT TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
CARTER WAS DEFINITELY OUTMUSCLED
AND OUTMANEUVERED BY MALCOLM AND
WE ENDED UP SHORT AGAIN SO
ANOTHER DISAPPOINTMENT.
WE'VE GOT TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL AND VOTE SOMEBODY OFF
AND PENNER AND I HAVE AN
ALLIANCE, BUT I'M STILL ON THE
FENCE RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH WAY I'M GOING
TO JUMP.
>> MAN, I THINK ME AND YOU KEEP
DENICE AROUND, I THINK WE'VE GOT
A LOYAL LADY.
>> I WANT TO KEEP DENICE.
I LOVE HOW HARD SHE WORKS.
>> YEAH, ME, TOO.
>> AND WITH KATIE I JUST DON'T
SEE A TON OF EFFORT.
IT'S LIKE -- IT'S JUST HARD FOR
ME TO WANT TO KEEP HER AROUND
BECAUSE OF THAT.
>> KATIE'S WORTHLESS.
SHE CAN'T DO ANYTHING IN THE
CHALLENGES.
SHE'S GOING TO SET US BACK.
WE'VE JUST GOT TO FIGURE OUT IS
IT BETTER FOR US TO GO WITH
PENNER IN THE MERGE OR NOT?
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T WANT A VETERAN
TO WIN.
>> ALTHOUGH I REALLY WANT KATIE
GONE, I'LL VOTE FOR PENNER.
>> I JUST WANT TO STICK WITH OUR
ORIGINAL LOGICAL THOUGHT OUT
PLAN OF STAYING TWO STEPS AHEAD.
>> WE'RE KICKING OURSELVES IN
THE BUTT FOR THE REST OF OUR
LIVES IF WE GET BLINDSIDED BY
HIM.
>> JEFF THINKS IT MIGHT BE A
GOOD IDEA TO MAKE A BIG MOVE AND
GET RID OF JONATHAN.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, YOU KNOW,
I THINK GOING INTO A MERGE WITH
PENNER MIGHT BE A GOOD IDEA
BECAUSE IF WE GO IN WITH HIM
EYES ARE GOING TO BE ON HIM, NOT
ON ME AND JEFF.
BECAUSE NOBODY WANTS A RETURNING
PLAYER TO WIN.
I'M GOING TO FOLLOW YOUR LEAD ON
THIS ONE, DUDE, OKAY?
>> I THINK WE NEED TO PULL THE
PENNER PUNCH.
WE JUST GOT TO MAKE SURE THAT HE
DOESN'T KNOW IT'S COMING SO HE
DOESN'T USE THE IDOL.
THAT'S ALL.
>> PENNER, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO
DO?
KATIE OR PENNER?
I MEAN KATIE OR DENICE?
>> WELL, I HATE TO LOSE KATIE.
BUT AT LEAST WITH DENICE WE HAVE
A CHANCE OF WINNING THE NEXT
ONE.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> WITH KATIE I DON'T THINK WE
DO.
>> TO WIN THIS GAME I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO MAKE BIG MOVES OUT OF
DESPERATION.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS.
IF YOU'RE DOWN NUMBERS YOUR BACK
STARTS TO GET PUT AGAINST THE
WALL.
SO KATIE'S GOT TO GO.
SHE'S NOT USE TO FEEL US.
I NEED HER GONE.
LOOK, I HATE TO BE DISLOYAL BUT
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT MY GUT IS
TELLING ME.
>> DENICE, ALL RIGHT?
WE ALL AGREE.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT?
YOU COOL WITH THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, LET'S FISH.
>> THAT WAS SOME SHADY (BLEEP).
WHAT'S HE REALLY SAYING?
>> HE'S OUT THERE.
HE'S WAY OUT THERE NOW.
>> WHEN I WENT OVER TO THE THREE
GUYS RIGHT AWAY WITHOUT ME EVEN
ASKING PENNER WAS LIKE "IT'S
DENICE, IT'S DENICE."
AND RIGHT AWAY I'M THINKING HE'S
FEEDING ME A BIG LINE OF B.S.
AND I'M NOT BUYING IT.
>> I'M STICKING -- I'M --
>> I TRUST DENICE A HELL OF A
LOT MORE THAN I TRUST -- HE'S A
WILD CARD!
PENNER'S WRITING SOMEONE DOWN.
THAT PERSON COULD BE ME FOR ALL
I KNOW BECAUSE I AM PHYSICALLY
NOT THE STRONGEST PLAYER IN THIS
GAME.
SO I'VE GOT TO HANG ON TO
WHATEVER IS WILLING TO KEEP ME
HERE.
AND IF WE'VE BEEN TALKING SINCE
DAY ONE, JEFF AND I, ABOUT
GETTING RID OF PENNER SO AS LONG
AS I CAN MAKE THEM BELIEVE THAT,
OH, MY GOD, THIS IS OUR TIME TO
GET RID OF JONATHAN THEN IT'S
GOING TO WORK OUT FOR ME AND
THAT'S GOING TO KEEP ME HERE AT
LEAST THROUGH THE MERGE.
>> SO YOU'RE READY TO GET
JONATHAN OUT OF HERE, HUH?
>> I'M SO DOWN, JEFF.
GET HIM THE (BLEEP) OUT OF HERE!
>> JUST PLAY ALONG WITH HIM FOR
NOW.
>> I'M SO CONFUSED RIGHT NOW,
DUDE.
KATIE VOTE FOR JONATHAN AND
JONATHAN'S GONNA VOTE FOR KATIE.
AND IT COMES DOWN YOU AND ME.
STRAIGHT UP.
I'VE COME INTO THIS GAME KNOWING
THAT I'M GOING TO HAVE TO LIE
AND KNOWING THAT I'M GOING TO
JEOPARDIZE MY INTEGRITY AND
CHARACTER SO I'M STILL WEIGHING
MY OPTIONS AND ALL OF THEM HAVE
TO DO WITH FURTHERING MYSELF IN
THIS GAME.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GET SCREWED
BY HIM.
>> LET'S GET IN THERE, MAN.
>> HOW YOU FEELING, BRO?
>> WE'RE STILL ON, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU SEEM --
>> I'M JUST TIRED.
>> WE'LL BE A STRONGER FOUR NOW.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, ALL RIGHT?
I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT IT.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> WHICH WAY YOU WANT TO SWING?
>> IT'S AN EASY PLAY TO VOTE
KATIE OUT.
THAT'S AN EASY DECISION.
THE HARD DECISION IS VOTING
JONATHAN OUT.
HE MIGHT BE NERVOUS AND PLAY THE
IDOL.
HELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN.
THIS IS A CRAP SHOOT.
YOU DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE GOING
TO STRIKE OUT OR HIT A HOME RUN
BUT YOU GO UP TO THE PLATE AND
SWING THE BAT.
>> Jeff: SO WHO TONIGHT TRULY
FEELS THEY'RE IN TROUBLE?
DENICE AND KATIE.
WELL, THAT WILL MAKE IT EASY
TONIGHT.
DENICE, WHY ARE YOU IN TROUBLE?
>> YOU KNOW I'M STILL THE NEW
GIRL ON THE BLOCK, SO TO SPEAK,
AND THAT'S A HUGE WORRY FOR ME
TONIGHT.
IT'S LIKE THE WORK FORCE, LAST
ONE HIRED; FIRST ONE FIRED.
BUT I'M TRYING TO SHOW MY TRIBE
THERE'S VALUE IN KEEPING ME FOR
A NUMBERS OF REASONS.
>> Jeff: KATIE, WHY WOULD YOU
BE IN TROUBLE WHEN YOU HAVE
DENICE WHO SEEMS LIKE AN EASY
VOTE?
>> BECAUSE I'M THE OTHER GIRL.
I DON'T PERFORM AWESOME IN
CHALLENGES SO IT'S LIKE I CAN
ONLY OFFER SO MUCH BUT I HOPE
THEY CAN GO OFF OF LIVING WITH
ME FOR 16 DAYS OUT HERE AND KNOW
THAT I'M LOYAL AND I'M WITH
THEM.
>> Jeff: PENNER, HAVING PLAYED
THIS GAME BEFORE, YOU KNOW HOW
OFTEN BLIND SIDES HAPPEN.
AND YET HERE YOU SIT SAYING "I'M
NOT IN TROUBLE TONIGHT."
>> I THINK ONE DOES NOT EVEN
WANT TO VOLUNTEER ONE'S SELF AND
GIVE ANYONE THE NOTION THAT,
HUH, MAYBE I SHOULD VOTE FOR
PENNER.
WHETHER I THINK I'M VULNERABLE
OR NOT, I WANT TO GIVE THE
IMPRESSION I FEEL PRETTY
CONFIDENT.
>> Jeff: JEFF, WAS LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL AN EASIER VOTE THAN THIS
ONE?
>> ALWAYS, YEAH.
EVERY ONE OF THESE VOTE IS GOING
TO HURT WORSE AND WORSE AS IT
GETS DEEPER.
THAT'S HOW WELL WE LIKE EACH
OTHER.
THAT'S HOW WELL WE GET ALONG.
THERE'S NOT GOING TO BE A VOTE
THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE A BLIND
SIDE.
>> Jeff: PENNER, INTERESTING
VOTE FOR FROM JEFF.
EVERY VOTE IS GOING TO BE A
BLIND SIDE BECAUSE WE LIKE EACH
OTHER SO MUCH.
>> HONESTLY, IT'S BEEN AN
EXTRAORDINARILY DRAMA-FREE ZONE
AND IF THERE'S GOING TO BE A
BLIND SIDE IT'S BECAUSE IT'S
JUST EASIER TO LET THE PERSON GO
AND HOPEFULLY THEY WILL
UNDERSTAND IT'S NOT PERSONAL,
IT'S STRICTLY SO THAT WE CAN
MOVE FORWARD A LITTLE FURTHER.
>> Jeff: SO IF IT'S YOU THAT
GETS BLINDSIDED IT'S A GOOD
STRATEGY.
>> I WOULDN'T LIKE IT IF THEY
DID IT TO ME BUT I WOULD
APPRECIATE THE GAME PLAY.
I WOULD TOTALLY UNDERSTAND IT
AND WOULDN'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
>> Jeff: JEFF, DO YOU PLAY ANY
GAME THAT'S SIMILAR TO
"SURVIVOR" IN TERMS OF STRATEGY?
>> NO.
THIS GAME SUCKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: IT SUCKS?
>> (LAUGHS).
>> Jeff: WELL, MEANING IT
SUCKS IN THE GREATEST WAY
BECAUSE IT'S COMPLICATED OR YOU
WISH YOU WEREN'T HERE AND YOU
WANT TO GO HOME.
>> NO, I THINK YOU KNOW WHERE
I'M COMING FROM.
YOU KNOW, THIS GAME IS --
>> Jeff: COMPLICATED.
>> IT'S VERY, VERY COMPLICATED
AND THAT'S WHY IT SUCKS BECAUSE
YOU TRY TO SURVIVE THE ELEMENTS
YOUR SNOW YOU CUDDLE WITH
PEOPLE, YOU TAKE ON FRIENDS AND
THAT'S WHAT SUCKS ABOUT THIS
GAME.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO BLIND
SIDE YOUR FRIEND BECAUSE YOU'RE
TOO GUILTY TO TELL THEM "I
REALLY DON'T WANT YOU HERE
ANYMORE.
REQUESTS THAT'S WHAT SUCKS.
>> Jeff: KATIE, JEFF JUST
PARAPHRASED WHAT THIS SHOW IS
ABOUT.
YOU HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER TO
BUILD A WORLD BUT VOTE EACH
OTHER OUT.
SO TONIGHT WHAT DO YOU VOTE
BASED ON?
>> I VOTE TONIGHT BASED ON
LOYALTY, BEING AROUND THESE
PEOPLE FOR THE LAST 16 DAYS.
AND WHEN I SAID MY WORD
INITIALLY I MEANT IT.
AND I INTEND ON STICKING WITH
THAT.
>> Jeff: PENNER, DOES THAT
MAKE KATIE A SITTING DUCK?
WHEN SOMEONE SAYS "THE WORD I
GAVE YOU IS MY WORD AND I'M
GOING TO STICK WITH IT"?
>> IS THAT GAME PLAY?
IS SHE JUST THROWING THAT OUT
NOW?
IS SHE SPEAKING TO SOMEBODY
HERE?
I'M NOT SURE.
THE REASON THAT IT'S SO
COMPLICATED IS NOBODY WANTS TO
BETRAY ANYBODY AND NOBODY WANTS
TO FEEL BETROYED.
THAT'S WHY THE BLIND SIDES
HAPPEN.
IF IT WAS ME TONIGHT AND THESE
FOUR DIDN'T GIVE ME THAT
OPPORTUNITY TO SCRAMBLE, MORE
POWER TO THEM BECAUSE THEY KNOW
THAT I WOULD DO ANYTHING IN MY
POWER TO MAKE THIS WORK OUT AND
IT MIGHT RICOCHET AND ONE OF
THEM WOULD GET VOTED OUT.
THEY WANT IT TO BE NEAT AND
CLEAN AND MOVE FORWARD.
THAT'S HOW I'M FEELING ABOUT THE
PERSON THAT I'M GOING TO VOTE
FOR.
THEY'RE GOING TO GET THE MESSAGE
LOUD AND CLEAR AFTER THE VOTE SO
DOING IT TO THEIR FACE ONLY ADDS
TO THE AGITATION FOR ALL THE
REST OF US.
>> Jeff: SO THIS IS GREAT
DRAMA.
EVERYBODY KNOWS A BLIND SIDE IS
COMING, THE QUESTION IS: WHO'S
IT GONNA BE?
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KATIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> GOOD-BYE, MY CUDDLE BEAR, YOU
ARE NOT TO BE TRUSTED.
>> RIGHT NOW YOU'RE THE WEAKEST
MEMBER OF THE TRIBE AND I NEED
TO KEEP THE TRIBE AS STRONG AS
POSSIBLE.
YOU'RE A GREAT KID.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KATIE.
PENNER.
>> OH!
>> TWO VOTES KATIE; ONE VOTE
PENNER.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES," KATIE.
THAT'S THREE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
KATIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, "SURVIVOR" IS ULTIMATELY A
GAME ABOUT NUMBERS.
THE GOOD NEWS IS IF THE FOUR OF
YOU ARE STRONG AND UNITED
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR" -- LISA IS NO
STRANGER TO THE FACTS OF LIFE.
>> YOU'RE MY REMIND ME OF MAMA
AND THAT'S HOW IT'S GOING TO BE.
>> YOU HAVE TO TAKE THAT WITH A
GRAIN OF SALT.
I COULD BE BEING PLAYED.
>> Jeff: AND A TWIST IN THE
GAME FORCES EVERYONE TO
SCRAMBLE.
(SCREAMING)
>> I BURIED THE IDOL THE FIRST
DAY I GOT HERE.
>> WE'RE NOW IN ALL NEW
TERRITORY FOR ALL OF US.
>> I GOT BLINDSIDED.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT A GOOD FEELING
BUT I CAME IN THINKING OH, I'M
AN ATHLETE, I'M SO STRONG, I CAN
HANDLE WHATEVER.
BUT OUT HERE IT IS NOTHING LIKE
YOU THINK IT IS ON T.V.
IT'S SO HARD BUT I MEAN IT'S
SUCH AN AWESOME THING FOR ME TO
BE ABLE TO SAY I WAS ON
"SURVIVOR"