Previously on Survivor, from the moment Pete and Abby found a hidden immunity item.
Oh my God, I found it!
They ruled the game with an iron fist.
Hopefully you're not going to be a double agent.
We got to keep Scoopin' on a little bit of a leash too.
They went into the merge with numbers.
We have Tandang now.
Everything's just a free ride, it's all.
And took out their enemies one by one.
Jobs bugger.
But everything changed when Scoopin' got tired of being at the bottom of their alliance.
How can we stay loyal to somebody who's not loyal to us?
At the last Tribal Council, Abby laid into Lisa.
I am not very sure about Lisa at this point.
I actually experienced more grace from the people that I was against than the people I was with.
But in the end, Lisa stayed true to her alliance.
And it was Scoopin' who joined the rebellion, taking out Pete and Abby's biggest ally.
Tenth person voted out in the third member of our jury.
Artis.
With their alliance crumbling, can Abby and Pete survive?
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
I feel bad for Artis.
Yeah, he didn't see that coming.
Trying to think about another game plan.
Yeah.
This happens when you fall asleep at the wheel.
Tribal Council disaster, basically.
Seriously, it's like, what the f***?
Like, I thought we had agreed that Tendang was supposed to be strong and make a big move together.
If we didn't do what we did tonight, none of us would have had a chance at the medal.
No.
So this is all of our chances.
It is.
Exactly.
Voting Artis off tonight was my first real big move.
But I don't believe you can win this game with just one big move.
I believe that there are several big moves that need to take place before the end of this game.
Well, I think the perfect scenario is to have all of us in the final six.
Oh my gosh, yes.
And then we shake hands and we say game on.
Fight it out.
Whichever way I go, I need to control this game as much as I can instead of letting somebody else determine my fate.
It's the only way I've ever lived my life and it's the way I'm going to play this game.
Honestly.
Honestly, I think you'll see that I never wavered from our alliance of four because I could walk away having not broken my word.
Even if it meant we were no longer, you know, had majority numbers.
Right.
How do you feel today, though?
Do you think you're going to align with them?
Well, it's very hard being in an alliance with Pete and Abby.
And I have never been good at breakups.
I have continued in relationships way too long just because I didn't want to hurt them.
And so that's what's felt comfortable out here.
A big part of who I am and who I have been is someone who feels comfortable to be used.
I feel like that for some reason I lost that trust in you and I can't be in an alliance with someone who really doesn't trust me.
You know what threw me off yesterday is when you said that the other side was more gracious to you than us.
They have gone out of their way to be kind to me and to encourage me.
Oh, it's just because they are smart and they want the numbers.
But, you know, it's all about forgiving around here, right?
And you do want to go to the end and you want to be on top of an alliance.
I do not want to be on the bottom of an alliance.
You know, if you go with them, your chances are very lean.
I get that.
But you know what, at this point, I'm willing to be sixth and feel good that the people I'm with aren't going to be calling me out at tribal council saying they don't trust me.
All right, fair enough.
I'm not going to try any harder.
If that's how you feel, there's nothing I can say.
Clearly you're already aligned with them.
So good luck.
The really wonderful thing is I do believe I'm taking control of my own destiny.
I think it's going to make a huge difference.
In the quality of my time out here, and it really sounds dramatic the rest of my life.
Come on in, guys.
Guys ready to get to today's reward challenge?
Yes.
For today's challenge, you'll be divided into teams.
Each team will have a total of three drums, one in each circle.
On my go, you'll race to flip your drum cymbal up while the other team tries to flip it back, cymbal down.
First team to get all three of their drums face up at the same time scores a point for their team.
First team to score three wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
Yes.
Today's reward is a thing of beauty.
You will be taken to a separate island where we have put together a spa day.
Gosh.
You'll start with a bath.
My hair.
You can wash your hair.
Yay.
Then how about a massage?
Oh man.
Pedicures and manicures.
And when you're nice and relaxed, chicken, beef, shrimp skewers, fried calamari, and some cocktails.
I know it's worth playing for.
We'll draw for teams.
We'll get started.
All right.
We have our two teams.
For the red team, Abby, Carter, Malcolm, and Pete.
For the yellow team, Penner, Denise, Lisa, and Scoopin'.
Here we go.
First round.
Carter taking on Penner.
We are playing to three.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Once you get all three of your drums face up, same time, you win.
Carter flips Penner's back over.
There you go.
Up here.
Penner flips the red team's over just in time.
Carter going quickly.
Carter go right first.
Done.
Red scores.
That a boy, Carter.
Red leads one zip.
Malcolm's coming up.
For the red team, he'll be taking on Scoopin'.
Survivors ready.
Go.
A little schoolyard game on Survivor.
Get to it, Malcolm.
Get to it.
Malcolm, go.
You got it.
Good.
Go.
Malcolm forgets to flip yellow back over, opening the door for Scoopin'.
Yellow scores.
We are tied.
1-1.
All right, next two.
Abby going to be taking on Lisa.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Leave it.
Abby, no.
Abby just flipped over one from the other team.
Abby.
Yellow scores.
Yellow leads 2-1.
Abby, are you clear on what's happening out here?
No, not really.
Last person from each team, Pete, will be taking on Denise.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Go, Pete.
All right, go get her, Pete.
Go.
Go, Pete.
You can get her right here.
Pretty even match so far.
Go.
Turn there.
Scores.
We are tied 2-2.
For the final round, we have Malcolm taking on Skookum in a rematch.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Skookum got him the first time.
Malcolm wants some revenge.
He could win it for his team right here.
Flip these two.
Watch yours.
It didn't flip.
Good.
No.
Skookum flipped over the red drum.
Win.
Skookum flipped the wrong one, but red team wins a huge reward.
Red team, nice job.
Boat's going to come in to take you to a nice survivor spa.
You'll have a bath.
You'll have a massage.
And then a nice afternoon lunch.
Carter, you might want to try a pedicure.
I need one.
Pedicure would be the feet, not the fingers, but either one will work.
Good eye.
Pinner.
Denise.
Skookum.
Lisa.
Got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Carter.
Abby.
Malcolm.
Pete.
Have a good afternoon.
Grab your stuff.
Get ready for the pick-out.
Yeah.
These are for us?
Wow, welcome.
We leave the challenge on this little boat, and we pull up to this amazing little stretch
of beach.
They have massage tables laid out for us, bathtubs, a couple of picnic tables under
some umbrellas.
I mean, life doesn't get much better than this.
Oh, my God, you guys.
Cheers again, please.
Cheers.
So we're all in agreement.
We're just going to enjoy this.
Yeah.
No strategy.
We're taking a day off.
Please.
We got all the young kids on a private beach.
I love it.
No old people.
I like that.
When I got here, I just kind of silenced the talk.
The strategy behind that is that I'm going to need to make a final three or final four
deal here pretty quick, and the people I want at the end, they're all sitting back at camp
right now while I'm sitting here just having spa day.
Doesn't matter.
Oh, baby.
Here we go.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you.
I love you.
Don't blink.
Oh, my God.
I'm in heaven.
Thank you.
They came with platters of delicious tapas foods, which is like little portions of food,
and we ate and ate and ate.
I'm eating like I've never seen food before.
I've been surviving on beans and sandy coconuts for the last 26 days, so today I literally
feel like a princess, a queen.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's get this going, too.
Pull.
It's a pretty good feeling to be away from the game.
That's why I agreed with Malcolm to not talk about strategy today, because I just need
a couple of hours just to relax, think about everything, and figure out what my next move
is.
I'm smart and I'm fit.
And those are two things that, with food, it's like a boost.
So next challenge, I'm going to be refueled and ready to kick some butt.
This was a great reward, you know, look.
What's this, guys?
Is this them?
They're back already.
Wow.
Look at their hair.
Come on up and fill us in.
It was, like, pretty amazing.
It was, like, the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
I felt like I was, like, in the desert and it was, like, an oasis.
So we were having a pretty quiet day, pretty relaxing, and then Abby came back from the
reward and was, like, ugh.
Oh, my stomach.
Ugh.
I felt like I had, like, a three-month baby cooking in my belly.
I was, like, eating, like, ugh, like a crazy woman.
It was, like, pretty amazing.
I felt like a princess.
Normally everyone's really super gracious when they come back from a reward, but Abby's
downright cruel.
She flaunted it and she wouldn't stop.
You know, it was breathtaking just arriving.
Like, the sight was just, like, something from, like, a cover of a travel magazine,
like, where you see, like, this beautiful blue sea and rocks and white sand and then
just, like, this gorgeous setup that's just, like, in the middle of nowhere.
It's just like an oasis.
Very neat.
It was gorgeous.
How are you feeling, Carter?
Never not.
What was your favorite part?
Um, the salt.
The salt.
You know, there's other things they eat out there.
How about you, Hans?
Your favorite part?
Um, the salsas.
There was a spicy one.
Then they had, like, the calamari with, like, the minty, yogurt-y, like, type of sauce.
It was really clutch.
Like, they had, like, this fruit basket that was to die for.
Mmm.
That's amazing.
It was so amazing.
Like, I felt, like, I was in paradise, literally.
I felt, like, I was a peasant here and then, like, a fairy just went, like, ding.
And then I became Cinderella.
Yeah.
Yeah, the rewards are good.
Abby has all the social grace of a Mack truck.
She has no understanding of how to talk to people.
Not any holding back for her.
No social skills.
Maybe what? Me?
Well, what's up with me?
I heard my name?
No.
We didn't see you.
It was a line of mice.
Oh, OK.
Oh, maybe I'm deaf.
No, you're not.
But I'm glad you guys stepped up to the plate,
because I am done with the kitchen.
OK.
Why?
Because I've been cooking for 26 days.
I'm over it.
And I'm leaving soon, so just enjoying my final moments.
OK, well, we'll continue to feed you during your final moments.
Oh, you guys are great.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, well, if you have to idle, which you do,
you're not going home for five days at least.
So do you not want to eat anything with it?
Oh, I don't want to cook, but I definitely do want to eat.
I don't want to starve to death.
You have lost your freaking mind, girl.
Part of me just thinks, that's fine.
Just let it piss everybody else off.
You know what?
Your time will come.
And I may not get to tell her anything
until I'm writing her name down, and it's that tribal council
that she's finally walking out.
And I get to say, you know what?
Winers are wieners.
You need to go home.
Oh, man, if we could make bacon and eggs.
Are you guys cooking?
Yeah.
Start them.
Because I'm out of the kitchen.
No more cooking for me.
OK.
Good to know.
Yep.
They just all ticked off at Abby.
That sucks.
I mean, I know Pete wants in, and I'd love to have him stay
and have him go, but I don't know how we can do that.
Oh, it could happen.
So when it gets to six, it's either game on,
or you make a plan.
If you want to wait that long, make a plan.
With a pretty easy vote in theory coming up,
my plan is to get a final four set up today
and just be able to kind of coast after this next vote
till the end.
I think it's fairly clear that you and Denise are probably
going to vote together.
But who else do we have for sure, for sure, for sure?
Lisa.
It's you and Lisa and you and Denise.
It's a very easy vote to make.
Lisa would have to be up for it.
We need to find out if that's going to be the case or not.
Malcolm proposed to me, him and Denise and you
and me in the final four.
He wants to go in the woods and shake on it.
Really?
Wow.
He thinks he can trust us the most.
It could be a big play.
If somebody wants to take you to the final four,
you have to say strategically, heck yes.
Because if you say no, then you could end up on man out.
And all of a sudden you're on the chopping block.
What do you think?
You know, we're at the point where we need to trust somebody.
So either we make a solid pact with Penner and Carter
or Malcolm and Denise.
Do you trust more Penner or Malcolm?
Oddly enough, Penner.
All right, we need to have a conversation with Penner.
I haven't said to anybody other than you two
that I want to go to the end with you two.
Well, I mean, first off, thank you.
That's cool and I appreciate that.
I personally am more than comfortable
taking care of business one thing at a time.
I really am comfortable taking care of Abby and Peter,
but I'm not that interested in committing anything to anybody.
Not yet.
Lisa respects me, and she said
I want to go to the final three with you and Scoopin'.
That's a great option, but it's too early for me to say
who I should go to the final three with.
I will continue to keep them close,
and if I get blindsided, more power to them.
I will go out with my head held high.
I don't want to get people squirrely
and get people starting to think
like we're getting ahead of ourselves.
We all agreed we'd go to six, and that's what we should do.
Penner didn't want to make that
we're true to the end kind of deal.
He said let's just kind of get rid of these two
and see how that shakes down.
I think he missed an opportunity.
I'm going to promise on my family
this is my final four and I'm not breaking it.
This is my word completely to the final four.
This is as serious a deal as you can make in this game.
This isn't just some quickie alliance,
wham, bam, thank you, ma'am, he's gone,
we're back on our own.
I stuck my neck out, I'm sticking with it.
If it works out, it could be the best thing
that's happened to me out here in the game.
Final four.
I've committed to a final four with Malcolm.
I'm not totally comfortable with it,
because he's a gamer, and that worries me.
But I felt I had to, I felt I didn't have a choice.
So it makes me a little nervous.
I want to be the one calling the shot,
so I'm going to do everything I can
to win the next Immunity Challenge.
Come on in, guys!
You guys ready to get to today's Immunity Challenge?
First things first, Scoop,
take back the Immunity Necklace.
Once again, Immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will maneuver a buoy
through a tangled rope.
The first five to finish move on to the next round,
where you will race to move your buoy along a balance beam.
The first three to finish move on to the final round,
where you will navigate your buoy
through a series of obstacles in the water.
First person to get to the finish wins Immunity
and a guaranteed one-in-seven shot at winning this game.
Losers go to tribal council, and after 27 days,
somebody will be voted out.
For me, it all comes down to this challenge.
Abby has the idol, so if I don't win Immunity,
I'm pretty much screwed.
So all I can do is fight right now, otherwise it's me.
Get it started.
Here we go, first round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It's very simple in design,
a little more difficult to execute.
You've got to get your buoy through this tangled rope
to the finish post.
The first five to get to their post move on to the next round.
Survivors may be out of this game for good.
Malcolm working quickly.
Pete making progress.
Penner getting close.
Malcolm close to the end.
Carter close to the end.
Denise is in this.
Abby doing a nice job.
Malcolm's first. Malcolm moving on.
Penner's moving on.
Looking for three more spots.
Scoopman moving on, two spots left.
Scoopman moving on, one spot left.
Down to Carter, Abby, and Pete.
Carter moving on, we have our five.
Denise, Carter, Penner, Scoopman, and Malcolm
moving on to the next round.
Abby and Lisa, no shot at immunity.
Next round, three people moving on to the final round.
Survivors ready.
Go!
Penner falls off quickly and has to go back.
Carter going to go on his belly.
Denise doing a nice job. Scoopman doing a nice job.
Penner really struggling.
Malcolm falls off, he's got to go back.
Denise is in this. Right now it's Denise, Carter, and Scoopman
with Malcolm trying to catch up and Penner out of it.
Scoopman is through. Scoopman moving on.
It's now Carter and Denise looking for those last two.
Carter is through, one spot left.
Malcolm got to pick it up.
It won't matter, Denise moves on to join Carter and Scoopman
in the final round.
All right, it is Carter, Scoopman, and Denise.
Here we go. Survivors ready.
Go!
Denise is to the boat first, out to a bit of a lead.
Carter right on their tail, and there's Scoopman.
It is very even off the top.
Carter's doing it all without leaving the boat.
Could be a good strategy.
Scoopman now picking up the pace.
Denise slowing down. It's hard to get around that boat.
Carter back in the water. Denise back in the water.
It is Scoopman, Carter, and Denise all very even.
Carter now with a bit of a lead.
Scoopman and Denise, you got to pick it up!
It is Carter, followed quickly by Scoopman and Denise.
Carter gets jammed up a little.
Scoopman now right on Carter's tail.
It's Carter and Scoopman. Here comes Denise.
Keep moving, Denise!
Got to manage that rope, or it will tie you up.
Scoopman now in the lead. Carter's hung up.
Carter's now got to catch Scoopman.
This is it. One last knot to maneuver.
Scoopman has a bit of a lead. Carter's right there with him.
It is Scoopman and Carter navigating that last piece of rope.
One knot. Who will it be?
Scoopman was in the lead. This is going to be very close.
Carter is through!
Carter wins Immunity, guaranteeing a spot in the final seven.
Carter, come on over. Nice job.
That was a close one.
That was a close one. Scoopman.
Carter is safe at tonight's Tribal Council, guaranteed a one-in-seven shot at winning this game.
As for the rest of you, after 27 days, somebody is going home tonight.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp. See you at Tribal. Congrats.
Thanks.
Nicely done, Carter.
Yeah, thanks, man.
Wow, nicely done.
That was fun, huh?
It was a good challenge.
How does it feel?
It feels good.
Today's challenge was a really fun challenge.
However, I didn't win it, and Peter did not win as well.
So it's basically Peter, Abby, and the Hidden Immunity Idol.
It's like an alliance of three versus six.
Let's just keep it simple.
Yeah.
Split three to three.
If she does not play the Idol, and it's a tie, then we all vote for her.
Got it.
Okay, and she'll walk home with the Idol.
But I'm assuming she will play the Idol.
And she'll go home.
Yeah.
Pete and Abby cannot win this game.
They don't have the numbers.
There's no reason to keep them around.
Their ship has sailed.
Now, could somebody surprise me and play an incredibly stupid move?
Maybe.
But I honestly believe all of us in the six are going to stay strong.
So if either Pete or Abby will go home, could it screw up?
Yeah.
But, you know, you could get hit by a car walking from your house to the post box, too.
You know, there are moves to be made.
Malcolm, he has power.
And he does.
And we have to win, send him home.
After last tribal, the whole game turned upside down.
Like, I went from the top of the pecking order all the way to the bottom.
And I'm not going to give in and be like, okay, guys, vote me out.
No, I'm going to try and get something going.
Malcolm, he's the biggest threat on the island.
He has an Idol.
And he needs to go home.
We'll be pitching this get rid of Malcolm idea to everybody, especially Scoop.
And he's kind of ditzy.
He doesn't really think before he does things.
He just jumps into it.
So I think he could actually be turned pretty easily.
But all I need is one person to flip.
It's going to be a whole new game.
All right.
I'm sure they're going to be splitting the votes.
So basically, you, Peter, and I, without him knowing, we would vote for Malcolm.
Well, Abby, let me just say, I mean, I think that sounds like a great plan.
And if we were still in an alliance where I'd given you my word, I would be totally on board for this.
But I told them I would vote with them.
But you started the game with us.
I did.
And I meant it.
But she's not sure because she feels like she gave the word to them.
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
So that's my plan.
I'm trying to stay alive.
I mean, you can tell me the truth.
I mean, I'm in a pretty good spot.
Why do you trust that Malcolm is not going to use his idol and try to blindside you?
Every single one of them has gone against me at one point or another.
So I don't trust any of them completely.
But they do trust me.
You see?
Because I have not betrayed them once.
And that is what I am sailing on.
You went far in the game.
You did well.
And you're not going to win this time.
All right.
Abby's playing her idol, so I have to scramble.
They're splitting the vote tonight, right?
If they split the vote and we get one person, we could take out Malcolm.
Just tell them that you're voting for me or whatever, and then that would be one vote less me.
Abby would play the idol, and whoever we all voted for would go home, which would be Malcolm.
Malcolm is the biggest person in this game right now.
Malcolm kind of controls the game right now, and he has an idol.
So this would take out two idols from the game, take out a big threat in challenges, and a big threat in social media.
I mean, would you be up for it?
We're both voting for Malcolm, no matter what.
Strategically, I want to get rid of him.
He's the biggest wild card in this game.
Yeah, because he's got the idol.
I have a deal to go to the final four with Malcolm, but now I'm starting to rethink whether that was a smart thing to do or not.
Because he's playing the hardest.
Malcolm's a threat in challenges, he's a smart strategic player, and he's liked by everybody.
So if I'm sitting next to Malcolm in the final three, I'm not sure I could beat him.
Vote for Malcolm, and he gets blindsided and he brings it home in his pocket.
And that would be huge.
I mean, you've never done me wrong this whole game.
So I'm not saying no.
The risk of changing it up again is it could backfire.
But do I anticipate our current alliance staying strong until the final four and having this happy ending?
It's not that likely in this game.
She had an incredibly cockamamie plan, which you could probably guess had something to do with you.
And I said, we have a plan. The plan's going to go into effect.
Apparently Pete and Abby have realized the easiest way to get somebody to flip is to throw my name out there and run me over tonight.
They just need one person to flop, and I'm going home.
I have the idol, but if nobody flips and I play that thing, I lose a lot of leverage moving forward.
Just to firm up exactly what we're doing.
Abby.
And Pete.
Okay.
Right?
Yeah.
This is the trickiest situation with the idol I've faced yet.
And I'm going to have to keep my wits about me tonight watching people and make the right decision.
Otherwise, I'm toast.
We'll now bring in the members of our jury.
R.C., Jeff, and Artis, voted out at the last travel council.
Aw.
Hi, baby.
A smile from Abby at a jury member.
Yes.
I love his green and yellow.
Malcolm, when you see Abby smile and say, hi, Artis, is it really about his colors,
or is that an early working of the jury?
I mean, thoughts about jury management cross your mind at this point in the game.
But right now, I'm more concerned about staying in the game than jury management.
Really?
You feel you're in trouble tonight?
My name seems to get kicked around a lot.
But tonight, the people I trust have to step up and prove it.
Because if one person jumps ship, yeah, you can send me home tonight.
So just simply from a strategic point of view,
how good a move would it be to take you out in one fell swoop?
I refuse to say it's a strategic move to get rid of me.
But I know it's going through people's heads.
I have to listen to it every day.
I have to read people's lips across the camp.
It's not hard to put the pieces together on what's going on.
Scoop, when somebody has an idol and you know it,
how do you navigate that?
It's a factor. You always think of the idol.
I mean, as you decide who you're going to vote with
and who you're going to vote for and who you're going to vote against,
you know, it's a factor.
And there's a lot of opportunities in every tribal council to vote whichever way you want.
And because it's Survivor, nobody really and truly knows.
So it's going to get a little crazy again.
Pete, what's it like to go from top dog, 10-day, never lost, to beat up?
It's not a good feeling.
I mean, I'm pretty much slated for execution right now,
but I've been trying all day.
Hey, let's make a deal. Let's work something out.
I mean, if one person came over, we could easily get rid of Malcolm.
He's got an idol.
So we'll see.
Abby, obvious question.
Regrets about how you handled the last tribal?
Absolutely. I'm very regretful about the last tribal.
But, you know, I never betrayed Lisa.
I just had doubt because of the way things happened, you know.
Do you think any of this can be cultural, Abby?
Absolutely, yeah, because English is not my first language,
and my attitude may be perceived as not the most gentle.
Mm-hmm.
Every single person is smiling at that.
Denise?
Absolutely. I've spent much of my life with many people
that English is not their first language,
and they're helpful, they're kind,
and there are just many of these qualities
that are just not a part of who Abby is.
Abby, is this the first time you've been in a situation
where you've had a group of people say,
wow, what's wrong with you?
Absolutely. I'm very loved back home by all my friends,
majority are Americans, and they love my passion
and everything that I had to bring to the table,
even my feistiness.
Does it make you feel isolated, or are you okay?
Can you handle that?
I'm very emotional right now
because I basically brought Lisa into an alliance with Peter and I,
and then because I doubted her, she just can't forgive me.
Can I just clarify that 100% forgave you?
It's just that I really need to find some people who will trust me.
Well, I understand that.
Abby, I'm really getting the feeling
that you don't feel understood by anybody.
No, I don't, but I don't know how to explain myself any longer.
It doesn't feel good, and I'm holding back my tears,
tears of feeling alone.
Denise, she has no numbers, she's all alone,
perfect person to take to the inn, easy win.
Easy win if that's the kind of game that you want to play.
We see that season after season, where people take kind of the dead weight,
they take the unlikable person, they take that they believe.
Wow, I never thought I was the unlikable person.
I'm just saying in seasons past, I'm not just putting you in that box, Abby.
But we've seen that, you know, we have.
I want to interrupt.
Yeah.
Abby, you didn't grasp that you're seen as unlikable?
I didn't, no, I seriously did not grasp that I was that hated in the game.
Abby, I'm beginning to believe very much that it's cultural,
because you didn't grasp that people laughing at you
was a sign in our culture that you're full of it.
Yeah.
Denise, you were just talking about wanting to play the game with good people
and not bring somebody like Abby to the inn,
which implies you are a good person.
It doesn't necessarily imply that I'm a good person.
It implies that in this game, I'm not going to bring a type of person with me
just so I can win by default.
It's like bringing someone to a poker game that's never played poker
just so you can steal their money.
That's enough. You don't need to do that anymore.
Abby, do you feel like you're just weathering a storm?
Yeah.
I've never had that much hatred towards me, ever.
It's not hatred. It's frustration.
Trying to communicate with you.
You know, we had come back from a reward challenge.
I was honest.
Abby, can you...
I was honest. Do you want me to lie about my feelings?
No. Can you let me finish for a moment, please?
What happened was you came back into camp gloating and pushing.
That's not true. I was sharing our experience.
And that's what I think you...
I don't understand what you're trying to get.
No. Can you pause, Abby, and let me finish, please?
And then you suddenly declared that you were basically on strike.
No, I was done cooking. I was cooking the whole time.
It's your turn to do it.
This would be a social...
I'll get water, and I'll get firewood.
This would be a social cue, Abby, where I'm trying to finish the sentence,
and you continue to interrupt me.
You are exaggerating. You know exactly what you're doing.
You're manipulating how I look in front of everybody.
Okay. I'm done. I can't explain.
Yeah, you're a psychologist. You know what you're doing.
I'm not a psychologist. I'm a therapist.
Whatever you are, you know what you're doing.
Now what are you feeling, Abby?
It's just really strange,
because apparently I'm an idiot that I don't get their cues.
But I'm not going to stop fighting. I'm going to try.
Well, any time there's somebody on the bottom,
there's this great opportunity to shuffle the game.
And with that, it is time to vote.
Abby, you're up.
This is for you. I hope you go home tonight.
You're going to be okay.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Thank you.
Any votes cast for Abby will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Abby does not count.
Abby does not count.
Pete, one vote Pete.
Malcolm.
Peter, two votes Pete.
We're tied, two votes Pete, two votes Malcolm, one vote left.
Eleventh person voted out and fourth member of our jury.
Pete, I need to bring you a torch.
Pete, chop his book.
Time for you to go.
Well, Abby, it would appear your back is up against the wall,
but as the cliche goes, anything can happen.
Thank you, Jeff.
Grab your stuff and head back to camp.
Good night.
Bye, you guys.
Oh, I got to get my torch.
Sorry.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
I'm not very good at this game.
Cut the crap.
New alliances tear apart old friendships.
Unbelievable.
Lisa once again lost her mind.
And the biggest villain in the game gets a taste of her own medicine.
It's like the worst day of my life.
I'm going to have to just turn my head around and I'm going to fight.
I felt bad for Abby.
She's crying and everybody ripped her apart.
I've kind of learned to deal with her, but, I mean, I needed to for my game.
Malcolm has a lot of power right now
He's definitely someone that they needed to get rid of,
but they didn't want to do anything with it.
I have a ton of regrets, but I feel good about how I left the island.
I'm not happy I left it, but I did what I could. gggggggggg