♪ ♪
>> Jeff: WE ARE ONE N ONE OF
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL AND REMOTE
LOCATIONS IN THE WORLD, THE
PHILIPPINES.
HERE, THOUSANDS OF ISLANDS
SCATTERED OVER THE SOUTHEAST
ASIAN SEA ARE HOME TO WATERS AND
RAIN FORESTS FILLED WITH
COUNTLESS ANIMALS BOTH BEAUTIFUL
AND DANGEROUS.
AMIDST THE SERENITY OF THIS
MAJESTIC RAND SCAPE, FURIOUS
STORMS CAN ARRIVE WITHOUT
WARNING.
IT IS HERE WHERE 15 AMERICANS--
ALREADY DIVIDED INTO THREE
TRIBES-- HAVE BEGUN THE
ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME.
>> I'M JEFF KENT.
I PLAYED 17 YEARS OF MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL.
I PLAYED IN THE WORLD SERIES
WHERE WE HAD SCREAMING FANS ON
THEIR FEET WITH BASES LOADED.
I'VE SEEN PRESSURE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A CHALLENGE
FOR ME, NO DOUBT.
I'M HOPING PEOPLE WON'T
RECOGNIZE ME.
>> YOU KNOW, I HAVE PEOPLE COME
UP TO ME ALL THE TIME AND ASK ME
ABOUT FRANKENSTEIN.
HE PICKED A LITTLE GIRL A
FLOWER.
HE STRANGLED HER AFTER HE GAVE
IT TO HER BUT, STILL, HE PICKED
HER A FLOWER.
THAT'S THE WAY I FEEL ABOUT
MYSELF, I COULD STRANGLE YOU OR
PICK YOU A FLOWER, IT DEPENDS ON
WHAT YOU PULL OUT OF ME.
>> MY NAME IS LISA WHELCHEL AND
I PLAYED A CHARACTER CALLED
BLAIR WARNER ON "THE FACTS OF
LIFE."
SHE WOULD NEVER IN A MILLION
YEARS BE ON "SURVIVOR" BUT I'M
VERY DIFFERENT.
I'M A HUGE FAN OF "SURVIVOR."
I'VE NEVER MISSED A SHOW.
I'M NOT GOING TO SAY I WAS ON
"THE FACTS OF LIFE" AS A KID.
I'M GETTING TO BE LISA.
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR" IS THE
MOST THRILLING ADVENTURE GAME ON
TELEVISION.
IT'S ALSO THE MOST DANGEROUS.
>> CAN YOU HEAR ME?
BOBBY JOHN?
>> GET HIM!
>> Jeff: OVER 24 SEASONS, MANY
OF THOSE WHO STARTED THE GAME
WERE UNABLE TO FINISH.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
>> Jeff: PULLED FROM THE GAME
WITH ONE QUESTION IN THEIR
HEARTS: WHAT COULD HAVE BEEN?
WHAT THESE CASTAWAYS DON'T KNOW
IS THAT THREE FORMER PLAYERS ARE
RETURNING FOR A SECOND SHOT TO
FINISH WHAT THEY STARTED.
>> THE LAST TIME I PLAYED--
>> WHOA!
RUSSELL?
YOU WITH ME?
>> "SURVIVOR" SMACKED ME IN THE
CHOPS.
>> RUSS?
YOU WITH US?
>> THIS TIME I'M SMACKING BACK.
EITHER THESE PEOPLE WILL RUN
WITH ME OR I'M GONNA HAVE TO RUN
THEM OVER.
THAT'S IT.
>> I GOT INJURED IN A CHALLENGE.
>> AN INFECTION THAT GOES INTO
YOUR BLOODSTREAM IS POTENTIALLY
FATAL.
>> IT WAS AWFUL.
>> COULDN'T HAVE DONE ANY
BETTER, COULD HAVEN'T FOUGHT ANY
HARDER.
DO YOU KNOW HOW ON FIRE I AM TO
WIN THIS THING?
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH I CAN TASTE
THIS?
YOU KNOW HOW I CAN ACTUALLY SEE
IT?
39 DAYS FROM NOW I'LL MAKE A
MILLION DOLLARS.
>> THE WHOLE 18 DAYS THAT I WAS
ON "SURVIVOR" IN THE AUSTRALIAN
OUTBACK WAS SUCH AN AMAZING EVEN
WHICH YOU ARE.
OUR TRIBE WAS WINNING AND THE
KILLING OF THE WILD BOOR WAS A
BIG ACCOMPLISHMENT BUT I THINK
THE WORLD SAW THAT ME FALLING IN
THE FIRE WAS MY GREATEST
FAILURE.
I DIDN'T SEE IT THAT WAY.
>> HE'S BURNED PRETTY BAD.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> KEEP HIS HANDS IN THE WATER!
(SCREAMING)
>> I THINK TO DWELL ON "WHAT IF"
WOULD CHEAT WHAT THE ADVENTURE
WAS FOR ME.
BUT I'M IN LOVE WITH THE FACT
THAT I'M ABLE TO COME OUT HERE
AND DO IT AGAIN.
>> Jeff: WILL THE VETERANS
HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO BE THE
SOUL SURVIVOR?
OR WILL A NEW CASTAWAY EMERGE TO
CLAIM THE MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE?
39 DAYS, 18 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR!
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR:
PHILIPPINES".
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THE GUY IN THE MAROON SHIRT,
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> JEFF.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU MAKE
ABOUT SEEING THREE TRIBES, NOT
THE NORMAL TWO?
>> PANIC.
YOU'VE ONLY GOT-- RIGHT NOW
WE'VE ONLY GOT FIVE TEAMMATES.
IF YOU'RE LOSING THE-- LOSING
TRIBE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THERE WILL BE A LOT OF PANIC
GOING ON REAL QUICK.
>> Jeff: GUY SMACK DAB IN THE
MIDDLE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> ZANE.
>> Jeff: ZANE, I KNOW YOU GOT
SOMETHING TO SAY.
>> I'M HAPPY WITH THREE TRIBES.
AS LONG AS IT AIN'T CELEBRITIES.
(LAUGHTER).
>> Jeff: .
>> I DO GET RECOGNIZED A LOT.
EVEN IF ONLY ONE PERSON
RECOGNIZE NASA WILL TRAVEL
THROUGH MY TRIBE SO I WANT TO
KEEP THIS SECRET.
>> Jeff: WOMAN IN THE BACK
WITH THE BLUE DRESS.
>> ROXANNE.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A SOCIAL GAME
FOR SURE BUT IT'S A PHYSICALLY
DEMANDING GAME.
HAVE YOU SEEN THE TOLL THIS GAME
CAN TAKE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THE WORST
YOU'VE SEEN ON THIS SHOW?
>> A GUY PASSING OUT IN THE
MIDDLE OF A CHALLENGE AND HE
JUST CANNOT RECOVER AND HE
DOESN'T WANT TO LEAVE THE GAME
AT ALL AND EVEN IN HIS CLEAR TO
YA HE'S LIKE "PLEASE, NO, NO
MATTER WHAT DON'T TAKE ME OUT OF
THE GAME."
>> Jeff: OVER 24 SEASONS MANY
PLAYERS HAVE SEEN THEIR SHOT AT
A MILLION DOLLARS CUT SHORT
BECAUSE THEY HAD TO BE EVACUATED
FOR MEDICAL REASONS.
THREE OF THOSE PLAYERS ARE
RETURNING FOR A SECOND SHOT.
THEY WILL BE PLAYING WITH YOU.
>> RIGHT BEHIND PROBST PULLS UP
ANOTHER BOAT WITH PREVIOUS
CONTESTANTS AND I'M SUCH A HUGE
FAN OF THE SHOW.
I'M THINKING TO MYSELF, OKAY,
ARE YOU DREAMING?
>> Jeff: RUSSELL SWAN
"SURVIVOR: SAMOA" PASSED OUT IN
FRONT OF ME DUE TO SEVERE
DEHYDRATION.
HIS HEART RATE PLUMMETED.
DOCTORS HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO
INTERVENE AND PULL HIM FROM THE
GAME.
JONATHAN PENNER IN "SURVIVOR:
FANS VERSUS FAVORITES" SUFFERED
A LIFE-THREATENING INFECTION.
MUCH TO HIS DISAPPOINTMENT,
DOCTORS PULLED HIM FROM THE
GAME.
GOING ALL THE WAY BACK TO SEASON
TWO. "SURVIVOR: AUSTRALIA"
HE WAS
TENDING TO THE FIRE, TOOK IN TOO
MUCH SMOKE, MOMENTARILY FAINTED,
HANDS FIRST INTO THE TRIBE FIRE
WITH SKIN DRIPPING OFF OF HIS
FINGERS WAS AIRLIFTED OUT,
PULLED FROM THE GAME.
ALL THREE OF THESE PLAYERS WERE
LEADERS ON THEIR TRIBE AND ALL
THREE HAVE ONE THING NONE OF THE
REST OF YOU HAVE: EXPERIENCE.
RUSSELL, HERE'S A BUFF AND MAP
TO YOUR NEW HOME.
YOU ARE ON THE BLUE TRIBE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
YOUR TRIBE NAME IS MATSING.
HEAD OVER AND SAY HELLO.
>> WHAT'S UP, FAMILY?
WHAT'S YOUR MAIM?
>> MALCOLM.
>> WHAT'S UP, MAN?
>> Jeff: JONATHAN PENNER,
YOU'RE ON THE RED TRIBE.
YOUR TRIBE NAME IS KALABAW, GO
SAY HELLO.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> I'M JONATHAN.
>> Jeff: THAT LEAVES YOU.
YOUR TRIBE NAME IS TANDANG.
GO SAY HELLO.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> WELCOME!
>> THE YELLOW TRIBE CAUGHT MY
EYE INSTANTLY.
I RECOGNIZED LISA FROM THE SHOW
THAT I WATCHED WHEN I WAS
GROWING UP.
>> I'M LISA, I'M A TPAOUPBLG FAN
OF YOURS!
>> HER SHOW NAME BLAIR ALMOST
CAME OFF MY LIPS.
>> HOW ARE YOUR HANDS?
LET ME SEE THEM.
ARE THEY GOOD?
>> THEY'RE GOOD.
TOOK A WHILE.
>> WE GOT YOU COVERED THIS TIME!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, YOU ARE ONE
OF THE ORIGINALS IN THIS GAME.
SEASON TWO.
WHAT'S IT FEEL LIKE TO BE BACK
HERE GETTING ANOTHER SHOT?
>> IT ALMOST FEELS LIKE THE
FIRST TIME AGAIN.
IT'S AMAZING TO BE HERE.
I MEAN, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S GOOD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOLS ARE IN PLAY THIS
SEASON.
YOU KNOW WHAT KIND OF IMPACT
THEY CAN HAVE ON THE GAME BUT AS
ALWAYS THE QUESTION IS WHERE ARE
THEY HIDDEN?
ALL RIGHT, THIS BOAT IS LOADED
WITH SUPPLIES THAT WILL HELP
MAKE YOUR LIFE A LITTLE EASIER.
YOU HAVE 60 SECONDS TO GATHER AS
MANY SUPPLIES AS YOU CAN, GET
YOUR RAFT AND GET OVERBOARD.
YOUR TIME STARTS NOW.
THERE'S FRUIT, THERE'S CHICKENS,
THERE'S WOOD.
GET WHAT YOU WANT, START GETTING
STUFF TOWARDS YOUR RAFT.
>> GUYS, GET A MACHETE IF YOU
SEE ONE.
COCONUTS.
>> PENNER YELLING OUT
INSTRUCTIONS.
>> TAKE IT UP, TAKE IT UP.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN UNTYING A LOT
OF KNOTS.
>> ANYTHING WITH A BLADE.
ANY BLADE.
>> Jeff: TEN SECOND LEFT.
>> BEFORE WHAT HAPPENS?
>> Jeff: BEFORE YOU'VE GOT TO
GET OFF THE BOAT, BROTHER,
YOU'VE PLAYED THIS GAME BEFORE!
>> YEAH!
>> BRING IT!
BRING IT!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, START
GETTING STUFF OVERBOARD, DROP
YOUR RAFTS.
>> OKAY, CUT IT!
CUT IT!
>> IS YOUR LEG OKAY, BUDDY?
GOT TWISTED?
>> Jeff: THE RED TRIBE LOSES
EVERYTHING AS THEIR RAFT GOES
IN.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL GET IT ALL.
GRAB THAT!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY OFF THIS
BOAT.
>> HERE, HERE!
>> Jeff: FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE.
GET OFF.
>> I GOT IT!
>> Jeff: LET'S LOOK FOR THE
CHICKEN.
>> I GOT HIM.
(SCREAMING)
>> KEEP COUNTERBALANCED, WE LOSE
EVERYTHING.
>> I GOT IT!
>> SEE YOU OUT THERE, GUYS!
GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
>> IS IT BROKEN?
IS IT TWISTD?
>> I HEARD IT POPPING, I DON'T
KNOW IF THAT WAS THE BAMBOO OR
MY KNEE BUT WE'LL SEE.
WE START WITH RETURNING PLAYERS
FROM INJURY AND WITHIN THE FIRST
THREE MINUTES MY KNEE IS PIN AND
I COULD HAVE POSSIBLY TORN MY
M.C.L.
THIS IS TOO BAD TO BELIEVE.
IF MY TEAMMATES SMELL BLOOD
THEY'RE GOING TO KICK ME OFF
THIS ISLAND REAL FAST.
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT THE FACT
THAT I AM JUST ABSOLUTELY
THRILLED TO BE HERE AGAIN.
I FEEL BLESSED.
WELCOME HOME, PEOPLE!
SO THE LAST TIME I PLAYED THIS
GAME I WAS IN THIS LEADERSHIP
ROLE BUT THIS TIME THE WHOLE
LEADERSHIP AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, LISTEN, I MEAN,
I TRIED TO DO THIS LEADERSHIP
THING BEFORE.
LOOK WHAT THAT GOT ME.
(LAUGHS)
SO NO LEADERS HERE, WE'RE ALL A
TEAM.
I DON'T CARE WHAT THEY DO.
THEY CAN VOTE FOR CHIEF, THEY
CAN VOTE FOR TWO CHIEFS, THEY
CAN VOTE FOR HIGH SUPREME.
WHATEVER IT IS, I'M NOT GOING TO
BE IT.
LET'S JUST GET THIS STUFF, GET
IT HERE AND WE'LL FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE WANT TO DO.
ALL RIGHT?
>> I'LL CARRY WHATEVER Y'ALL
WANT ME TO.
>> MY PLAN IS TO FEEL THEM OUT
AND IF THIS LEADERSHIP THING
COMES UP THROW IT AT THE GUY WHO
DOESN'T REALIZE THAT LEADERSHIP
IS A GOOD THING.
BECAUSE THERE'S ALWAYS SOME GUY
WHO'S AN IDIOT.
"I THINK I SHOULD BE THE
LEADER."
"OKAY, YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE THE
MAN.
THANK YOU, MY HERO!"
JUST WATCH THEM CRASH AND BURN.
DUMBNY.
(LAUGHS)
THE IDEA IS YOU WANT IT TO JUST
BREAK WHERE IT'S SCORED.
WHAT I WANT IS SOMETHING
UNDERNEATH THAT'S GONNA SIT ON
THIS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO TRY TO CUT ON
THE KNUCKLE?
>> YOU DON'T?
>> NO!
KNUCKLE IS THE HARDEST PART TO
CUT.
>> WHAT WE'LL DO, HAVE THE FIRE
PIT DOWN LIKE CLOSER TO THAT
PART OF THE TREE DOWN THERE.
>> RUSSELL KEEPS TELLING US THAT
HE'S NOT THE LEADER BUT HE'S THE
ONE SITTING THERE SAYING "OKAY,
GUYS, TAKE A FIVE-MINUTE BREAK,
DRINK SOME WATER."
LIKE, OKAY, WE HAVE TO LISTEN TO
HIM.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING.
>> (LAUGHS)
>> WE DO NEED A LEADER BUT I
JUST FEEL LIKE WE SHOULD ALL
JUST WORK TOGETHER NOT LIKE FOR
HIM.
>> IF ANYBODY WANTS TO HAVE AT
THAT!
>> YOU WANT TO GIVE THAT SHOT.
>> I LIVED IN MICRONESIA FOR A
YEAR.
I'VE DONE IT BEFORE.
I LIVED IN MICRONESIA TEACHING
E.S.L. TO ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
KIDS.
I WASN'T ROUGHING IT ANYTHING
LIKE THIS BUT I CAN DO THE FIRE,
I CAN DO PALM FRONDS, COCONUTS,
THINGS LIKE THAT.
TAKE IT SLOW AND SMOOTH, GET A
FEEL FOR WHAT YOU'LL BE DOING.
JUST GETTING THE WOOD WARM.
A.
>> THEY'RE SHARING FIRE?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S STARTING TO SMELL.
>> GOT A LITTLE SMOKE, KEEP
GOING, ATTA BOY!
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE IT.
YOU'RE STILL SMOKING, WE GOT IT.
>> OH, MY DAMN!
>> COME ON!
>> WHO'S STARTING THE FIRE?
>> GRASS.
>> WHOA!
>> RUSSELL--
>> COME IN, NICELY DONE!
>> KICKED SOME ASS.
>> THANK YOU, PEOPLE.
GUESS WHAT WE HAVE?
>> FIRE!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> WE MADE FIRE IN THE FIRST,
LIKE, 45 MINUTES WE WERE HERE.
I WOULD GIVE MY BUTT TO KNOW IF
ANYBODY ELSE HAS GOT FIRE.
YOU JUST CAN'T BEAT IT.
>> BROTHER KNOWS HOW TO WORK.
JUST TELL ME.
I'LL WORK FOR YOU, JUST TELL ME
WHAT TO DO SOMETIMES.
>> HIGH FIVE ALL THE WAY AROUND.
>> YOU'VE ALWAYS GOT TO BELIEVE
IT.
>> DAY ONE, WE GOT THE FIRE
GOING.
RUSSELL IS THE ONE WHO DID IT
WHICH WORKS OUT IN A WAY BECAUSE
HE WANTS TO BE THE LEADER SO BAD
AND EVERYTHING HAS TO BE WAY HE
WANTS IT DONE.
SO WHEN HE WAS THE ONE WHO
ACTUALLY GOT THE FIRE GOING, IN
A WAY A LITTLE BIT OF A TARGET
CAME OFF MY BACK BECAUSE I'M NOT
A THREAT TO HIM.
>> RIGHT NOW I THINK THE GAME IS
JUST BE NICE TO RUSSELL AND MAKE
HIM FEEL GOOD ABOUT BEING THE
LEADER.
>> WHATEVER.
>> I LET HIM BUILD A FIRE.
SO IT'S KIND OF A BLESSING HE'S
THE ONE WHO PULLED IT OFF AND
HE'S ON CLOUD NINE, WHATEVER
PLANET HE'S LIVING ON.
>> YEAH!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THAT WAS JUST FANTASTIC.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> WHAT A BOUNTIMENT LET'S GET
EVERYTHING OFF AND THE THREE OF
US CAN MAYBE JUST GET IT UP
ABOVE THIS TIDELINE.
>> I THINK I LEFT MY KNEE AT THE
BOAT GETTING OFF.
WE LAUNCHED THAT BOAT, I WAS
TRYING TO HOLD OUR GEAR ON THE
BOAT ITSELF AND MY LEG GOT STUCK
AND I GOT FLIPPED OVER AND--
I'VE PLAYED HURT MY WHOLE
CAREER.
I'VE HAD SURGERIES ON MY KNEES.
GETTING ON THIS SAND AND WALKING
AROUND RIGHT NOW, MY KNEE WANTS
TO BUCKLE ON THE INSIDE.
SO I AIN'T-- IT JUST DID IT
AGAIN.
I AIN'T FEELING TOO GOOD.
THAT MEDIAL LIGAMENT I THINK IS
HURT.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
I DON'T WANT ANYBODY TO KNOW I'M
HURT.
I'M TRYING TO PLAY IT OFF AS
BEST I CAN FOR NOW.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> WHAT ARE WE THINKING ABOUT
RIGHT IN HERE?
>> YEAH, THAT WILL WORK.
>> READY?
ONE, TWO, THREE.
NICE.
NICE, GOOD JOB.
>> I'M LOOKING AT THIS AS MY
JOB.
THIS IS EARLY GAME, IT'S A
MARATHON.
BECAUSE THIS IS SUCH A CRAZY
TWIST OF THE GAME STARTING WITH
THREE TRIBES THROWS THE WHOLE
THING UP IN THE AIR.
TO GET TO DO THIS AGAIN, THIS IS
SO MUCH FUN FOR ME AND SO
REWARDING.
THE OPPORTUNITY TO COME OUT HERE
AND DO THIS, EVEN WITH THESE NEW
FOLKS, THEY SEEM VERY COOL.
>> IT'S RIGHTEOUS, Y'ALL.
>> IS IT GOOD?
>> TAKE A ZIP OF THIS.
>> I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
KICKING SOME A ++S WITH THEM.
IT'S VERY MOVING.
IT'S MOVING TO BE HERE.
IT'S MOVING TO BE DOING THIS
AGAIN.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL THING.
>> I KNOW JONATHAN, HE'S A GOOD
GUY.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
BUT IF ANYBODY'S GOING TO WIN
THIS GAME IT OUGHT TO BE ONE OF
US.
HE'S A VETERAN.
DO WE WANT A VETERAN TO WIN OR
ONE OF US TO WIN?
>> HE'S RIGHT.
>> SURVIVAL SKILLS HE BRINGS TO
US, MAYBE WE USE HIM FOR A
COUPLE DAYS, AFTER THAT MAYBE WE
THINK ABOUT, OKAY.
>> WE'VE GOT THE HANG OF THIS.
>> WE'VE GOT SHELTER, FIRE,
WE'VE GOT FOOD.
>> I AGREE.
>> NOT THAT JONATHAN'S NOT A
GOOD GUY BUT THE MERE FACT THAT
HE'S A RETURNING THIRD-TIME
PLAYER, I THINK HE'S HAD HIS
TIME AND I THINK THAT I'D LIKE
TO SEE ONE OF US WIN IT IF IT'S
POSSIBLE.
SO HE'S OUT AS SOON AS WE CAN
GET HIM OUT.
(LAUGHTER)
>> GOT IT!
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> WHEN I LOOKED AT THE THREE
DIFFERENT TRIBES, MY TRIBE IS
THE ONE I WOULD HAVE PICKED.
I THINK WE HAVE A REALLY GOOD
MIX OF BRAINS AND BRAWN.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
SAID MAYBE YOU SHOULD NEVER PLAY
AGAIN BECAUSE NOW YOU'RE OPENING
YOURSELF UP TO THAT-- THE LEGEND
OF WHAT I WAS TO WHAT I AM
TODAY.
SO IT'S A HUGE RISK.
BUT IT'S WHAT DRIVES ME.
>> CLEAR BACK THERE?
CLEAR?
>> I THINK THAT WE SHOULD MAYBE
BE AROUND HERE, WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
>> I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT I THINK
BUT.
>> I THINK AROUND HERE IS
BETTER.
>> I'M DEFINITELY AN ALL OR
NOTHING TYPE GIRL AND I'M HERE
TO PLAY THE GAME NO MATTER WHAT.
I DEFINITELY CLICKED WITH
CERTAIN PEOPLE.
ABI IS FANTASTIC AND I TRUST
HER.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
TRUST EVERYBODY IN THIS GAME BUT
YOU HAVE TO TRUST SOMEBODY.
I'M SO HAPPY YOU'RE ON THE SAME
TRIBE WITH ME.
>> I KNOW!
I WAS TELLING EVERYONE THAT
YOU'RE THE SEXY LIBRARIAN.
WHAT DO YOU DO IN NEW YORK?
>> I'M AN EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT.
>> I USED TO BE ONE!
>> I'M TELLING PEOPLE I'M AN
EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO KNOW I'M A
BANKER.
THERE'S SUCH A NEGATIVE
CONNOTATION ABOUT BANKERS AND
WALL STREET BUT TO BE A GREAT
INVESTMENT BANKER YOU HAVE TO
HAVE THE KILLER INSTINCT.
BECAUSE YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO BE ON
YOUR TOES IN NEW YORK, HAILING A
CAB IN THE RAIN IN SIX-INCH
HEELS.
SO IF I CAN HANDLE WALL STREET I
CAN CERTAINLY HANDLE "SURVIVOR."
>> WHO SHOULD WE BRING IN OUR
ALLIANCE.
>> I LIKE SKUPIN.
>> SKUPIN?
>> HE'S DONE THIS BEFORE.
>> YEAH, HIM FOR SURE.
YEAH.
BUT WHO ELSE?
I REALLY THINK THAT PETER'S
STRONG AND HE'S A LITTLE BIT--
>> DUMB?
>> (LAUGHS)
YEAH, WE SHOULD HAVE HIM.
YOU AND I FOR SURE.
>> WE COULD WIN TOGETHER.
>> TOGETHER.
>> ABI AND I JUST CONNECT ON A
GOOD LEVEL AND SO HOPEFULLY THAT
CONTINUES THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE
GAME.
BUT WHO KNOWS HOW LONG IT WILL
LAST.
>> OKAY, WE'RE ON THE SAME PAGE.
>> I CAME TO THE UNITED STATES
ABOUT 12 YEARS AGO.
I HAVE A VERY STRONG BRAZILIAN
ACCENT.
>> CAN YOU CUT THIS IN HALF FOR
ME, PLEASE?
HOPEFULLY I CAN USE IT AS A
FLIRTATIOUS TOOL.
MAYBE MY ASS IS TOO BIG.
YEAH, I THINK IT IS!
MY BIG BRAZILIAN BOOTY.
>> ABI KEEPS STARING AT ME AND I
THINK THAT'S GOING TO BE A BIG
ADVANTAGE.
SHE DEFINITELY LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
READY TO PLAY SOME EVIL GAMES.
SHE'S PRETTY HOT.
SHE COULD DEFINITELY DO SOME
DAMAGE.
>> SO THAT'S IT.
>> I JUST LIKE-- I DON'T TRUST
THE OLDER LADY AND-- LET'S GO
BACK UP SO THEY DON'T GET
CURIOUS.
>> IT'S DAY ONE, ME AND ABI AND
PETE, WE ALREADY HAVE AN
ALLIANCE AND I THINK IT'S A
PRETTY SOLID ALLIANCE.
BUT WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR IS A
STRONG FOUR SO WE'VE GOT THE
MAJORITY.
I'M A HUGE FAN OF THE SHOW AND I
REALLY DO THINK THAT WE CAN'T
LOSE WITH YOU ON OUR TEAM AND I
DON'T THINK WE CAN LOSE WITH YOU
IN AN ALLIANCE.
SO WE WERE THINKING ABI, PETE,
ME AND YOU.
>> WE MIGHT AS WELL START
SOMEWHERE, THAT SOUNDS LIKE A
GOOD PLACE TO START.
MY STRATEGY COMING INTO THIS WAS
MAKE SURE THAT YOU GO WITH THE
GAME.
IF YOUR TRIBE IS MOVING SLOW, GO
SLOW WITH THEM.
DON'T BE THE PERSON THAT JUST
JUMPS OUT IN THE LEAD.
>> I THINK YOU'RE FANTASTIC.
>> THANKS.
>> GOOD, I'M GLAD I'M ON YOUR
SIDE.
>> THIS IS A LITTLE BIT FOREIGN
TO ME, THE THREE-MAN ALLIANCE.
BUT THE THREE YOUNGER PEOPLE
MOVE FAST.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO MOVE FAST
WITH THEM OR I'M IN BIG TROUBLE.
GROUND, TAKE A QUICK LOOK AT IT,
SEE IF YOU'VE GOT SPIDERS OR
SCORPIONS OR ANTS ON IT.
IN TEXAS, EVERYTHING BITES.
>> WHAT PART OF TEXAS ARE YOU
FROM?
>> RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
AUSTIN.
>> AUSTIN'S NOT SO BAD.
>> I GOT A RANCH DOWN SOUTH,
SOUTH OF SAN ANTONIO.
>> YOU'LL BE QUITE THE USEFUL
FELLOW AROUND HERE.
>> COMING INTO THE GROUP AND
LOOKING AROUND AT THE REST OF
THEM I DON'T SEE ANY OTHER
TATTED UP PEOPLE WITH SPIKEY
HAIR.
>> I SHOOT WITH A BOW.
>> HE'S FROM THE SOUTH.
I'M FROM THE SOUTH.
HE HAS A RANCH AND I GREW UP
RIDING FOUR WHEELERS, FISHING.
I'D FIGHT ANY BOY IN THE TRAILER
PARK THAT WOULD EVER CHALLENGE
ME.
HERE, I'LL TAKE OVER FOR A
MINUTE.
MAYBE ME AND JEFF CAN PULL SOME
SOUTHERN ROOTS TOGETHER AND BOND
ON THAT.
>> MIKE, HAND ME THAT-- CAN YOU
HAND ME THE ONE YOU THREW AWAY
FOR A HAMMER?
>> YEAH.
>> BEING A BASEBALL PLAYER COULD
BE A DISADVANTAGE TO ME.
THERE'S A LOT OF BAGGAGE THAT
GOES ALONG WITH IT.
YOU MADE MONEY SO YOU DON'T NEED
THE MONEY.
BUT THIS GAME IS NOT ABOUT WHO
DESERVES A MILLION BUCKS BECAUSE
YOU'RE IN DEBT OR DON'T HAVE A
LOT OF MONEY.
>> YOU GOT IT, JEFF!
>> COME ON!
>> I'VE BEEN A FAN OF THE SHOW
FOR A LONG TIME AND I WANT TO
PLAY THE GAME.
I'VE BEEN OUT OF BASEBALL FOR
FOUR YEARS NOW AND I LOVE TO
COMPETE.
I DON'T NEED THE MILLION BUCKS,
BUT I'D SURE LIKE TO BE THE SOLE
SURVIVOR.
ARE YOU A FAN OF THE SHOW?
>> I AM A FAN OF "SURVIVOR."
>> I JUST CAN'T IMAGINE YOU
SITTING AROUND ON YOUR RANCH
WATCHING "SURVIVOR."
>> WELL, IT WAS KIND OF A DARE
FROM A BUDDY OF MINE.
THEY HAD AN AUDITION IN AUSTIN
SO I SENT IN A MOTOCROSS TAPE.
>> TELL US ABOUT YOUR MOW TOE
CROSS.
>> I USED TO SPEND TIME WITH A
GUY WHO WAS REALLY INTO BASEBALL
AND I KNOW WHO JEFF KENT IS.
BUT THERE'S BEEN NO MENTION OF
HIM BEING A FORMER PROFESSIONAL
ATHLETE WHO'S MADE PROBABLY $30
MILLION IN HIS CAREER.
>> WELL, I'M NOT ONE OF THE PRO
GUYS.
I DON'T MAKE MONEY RACING
BIKING, IT'S A HOBBY.
HOW I MAKE MY MONEY IS SELLING
MOTORCYCLES.
>> I DON'T THINK THE OTHER TRIBE
MEMBERS KNOW AND I THINK JEFF
LIKES IT THAT WAY.
BUT I WILL TELL HIM THAT I KNOW.
AS SOON AS IT BACKS VALUABLE TO
ME.
>> YOU'RE GETTING YOUR PANTS
WET.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> TAKE IT OFF.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TAKE IT OFF!
>> MAKE HER GET NAKED!
(LAUGHTER)
>> I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT OH, I
WOULD SO LOVE TO BE ON
"SURVIVOR."
NOT ONLY HAVE I EVER NOT MISSED
A SEASON, I'VE NEVER MISSED A
SHOW.
YOU'RE FROM TEXAS?
>> BORN AND A RAISED.
>> I DON'T PLAN TO VOLUNTEER
THAT I WAS ON A TELEVISION
SERIES BECAUSE NOBODY WILL GIVE
ME A MILLION DOLLARS BECAUSE
THEY FEEL LIKE I'VE ALREADY HAD
MY 15 MINUTES OF FAME.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF I HAVE WHAT
IT TAKES TO PLAY THE GAME IN A
CUTTHROAT WAY SO I HAVE TO PLAY
TO MY STRENGTH.
I'M TRYING TO CONNECT WITH EACH
PERSON ON A ONE-ON-ONE BASIS.
>> I ACTUALLY HAVE A MINISTRY
FOR MOMS SO I WRITE BOOKS AND GO
AND SPEAK TO GROUPS OF MOMS OF
YOUNG CHILDREN AND ENCOURAGE
THEM.
>> HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN DOING
THIS FOR?
>> ABOUT TEN YEARS.
>> WOW.
>> WE FILMED THE LAST EPISODE OF
"THE FACTS OF LIFE" IN MARCH OF
'88, I GOT MARRIED IN JULY OF
'88 AND I LEFT THAT BEHIND.
I LOST THE MONEY I MADE ON "THE
FACTS OF LIFE."
I HAD A BUNCH OF MONEY INVESTED,
A LOT OF IT KIND OF WENT THE WAY
OF THE '80s CRASH AND THAT IS
JUST-- HAS HAUNTED ME FOR 20
YEARS.
>> FIRE, WATER, SHELTER.
WHO KNOWS HOW TO MAKE A FIRE?
>> I'LL GIVE IT A TRY.
BEING ON "SURVIVOR" AT THIS
SEASON OF MY LIFE IS A GOD SEND
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN RUNNING AND
RUNNING FROM THE TIME I WAS A
LITTLE KID TO SLOW DOWN AND GO
INSIDE AND TO FIND OUT, OKAY,
WHAT-- WHO AM I?
AM I MORE THAN A MOM?
AM I MORE THAN A CHILD STAR?
>> I THINK SHE'S GETTING THE
FIRE GOING.
>> I HOPE SHE GETS IT.
>> SO I'M EXCITED ABOUT THE GAME
BECAUSE I LOVE THE GAME.
BUT ON A WHOLE OTHER LEVEL I'M
REALLY EXCITED ABOUT WHAT'S
GOING TO CHANGE INSIDE ME.
>> LISA, WE'RE GOING TO TAKE--
YOU WANT TO COME WITH?
>> WELL, I DON'T MIND KEEPING
WORKING ON THE FIRE.
IF YOU WANT ME TO COME WITH YOU,
I WILL.
>> IF YOU GET A FIRE GOING,
YOU'RE THE QUEEN.
>> I WILL KEEP WORKING ON IT.
>> LISA IS LIKE THIS VERY
BEAUTIFUL OLDER WOMAN AND IT'S
LIKE SHE DOESN'T HANG OUT WITH
US AND THEN SHE'LL GO OFF ON HER
OWN.
SO I THINK IT'S HARD TO TRUST
LISA AND I THINK IT'S EASY TO
SORT OF MAKE HER A SCAPEGOAT.
I DON'T TRUST HER.
I THINK SHE SAYS THINGS TO SORT
OF, LIKE, PUT YOU OFF AND MAKE
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU REALLY LIKE
HER AND SHE'S LIKE JUST HERE TO
SMILE AND HAVE A GOOD TIME.
BUT SHE'S A SMART PLAYER.
DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE LISA AT
ALL.
>> LISA'S WAY FAMOUS.
LIKE, WORLDWIDE FAMOUS.
LIKE HER SHOW WAS ON EVERYDAY
FOR YEARS AND YEARS AND YEARS
AND YEARS AND SHE SHOULD BE
PLAYING THAT TRUMP CARD BECAUSE
YOUNG IMPRESSIONABLE PEOPLE
MIGHT BE, WOW, I'M KIND OF WOW.
BUT MAYBE HER SHOW WAS SO OLD
THEY WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW WHO SHE
IS ANYWAYS EVEN IF SHE TOLD
THEM.
>> FOUR OF US DEFINITELY.
>> YES.
>> WE NEED AN ALLIANCE NAME.
(LAUGHS)
>> I DON'T KNOW HER STRATEGY
FULLY FOR NOT REVEALING WHO SHE
IS BUT I WANT TO!
>> I RECOGNIZED YOU INSTANTLY.
>> YEAH, OKAY, GOOD.
>> I'D LOVE LISA TO STAY BECAUSE
I MORE FROM AN AGE STANDPOINT
FIT WITH HER AND I'M SORT OF
WAITING FOR HER TO START
PLAYING, TO START BONDING.
HER NAME COMES UP IN A
DISCUSSION OF WHO DO YOU WANT TO
BE VOTED OUT FIRST.
I DON'T WANT IT TO BE HER.
BUT IF I'M GOING TO GET WITH THE
TEAM THAT'S PLAYING THE GAME
I'VE GOT TO GO WITH THE GAME.
AS OPPOSED TO YOUR HEART.
>> WHERE DID YOU SAY YOU WERE
FROM?
>> VIRGINIA.
>> VIRGINIA?
>> YES, MA'AM!
I WAS ALWAYS THE KIND OF PERSON
THAT SCHOOL DIDN'T MAKE A WHOLE
LOT OF SENSE TO ME.
IF I WAS GOING TO DO SOMETHING
FOR EIGHT HOURS A DAY I WANTED
TO GET PAID, YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN?
I DROPPED OUT WHEN I WAS ABOUT
17 AND I WENT TO WORK AT A
JUNKYARD.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE IN MY TRIBE
BECAUSE I WAS REALLY CURIOUS
ABOUT YOU.
>> I'M A LICENSED SEX THERAPIST.
BEING A THERAPIST, I'M CURIOUS
ABOUT ZANE BECAUSE AT FIRST YOU
GO, GOD, THIS GUY IS TROUBLE BUT
THEN YOU LOOK CLOSER AND YOU GO,
OKAY, WAIT A MINUTE, LOOK CLOSER
AT THOSE TATTOOS.
HE'S LOST SOMEBODY, THERE'S A
DEATH DATE OF SOMEBODY ON HIS
ARM AND HE'S GOT THE SERENITY
PRAYER ON HIS HANDS SO PART OF
ME IS KIND OF HOPING, THIS GUY'S
GOT SOME STORY.
IF NOTHING ELSE, I'M CURIOUS
ABOUT HIS STORY.
>> HEY, AND YOU KNOW, IT AIN'T
TOO EARLY TO MAKE ALLIANCES.
>> I LIKE YOU.
>> I LIKE YOU ALREADY.
>> I LIKE YOU ALREADY, AND I
WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOUR
TATS.
I LIKE IT, ZANE.
I THINK WE'VE GOT A PLAN.
>> NICE TO KNOW YOU'RE IN THE
CORNER.
I'VE WORKED IN RETAIL A LOT, IN
A JUNKYARD, NOW I'M RETREADING
TIRES.
BUT ALL THE JOBS I'VE HAD, IT
GIVES YOU A CHANCE TO BE ABLE TO
INTERACT WITH EVERYBODY.
FROM A CRACKHEAD SELLING $3
WORTH OF CANS TO A MILLION
DOLLAR BUSINESSMAN.
LET'S MAKE US A LITTLE PILE
RIGHT HERE.
ALL THE JOBS, THEY ALL FORM
TOGETHER TO MAKE ME THE PERFECT
"SURVIVOR" PLAYER.
PROMISE ME AND YOU, I THINK
NOW'S THE TIME.
>> YEAH, I THINK SO, TOO.
>> YOU SEEM TOUGH AS MY TATTOOS.
I THINK ME AND YOU CAN DO IT,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> OKAY, I THINK SO, TOO.
>> YOU IN MY CORNER NOW?
>> YES, YES, I AM.
ZANE'S INTERESTING.
ZANE'S THE GUY THAT I DIDN'T
THINK THAT WOULD BE MY FAVORITE.
BUT I FEEL LIKE ZANE'S PRETTY
HONEST WHEN HE'S WITH ME BUT
ZANE COULD JUST BE A REALLY GOOD
PEOPLE PERSON!
HOW ARE WE DOING ON ALLIANCES?
>> I HAVEN'T FORMED ANY, HAVE
YOU?
>> NO, I HAVEN'T.
>> WELL, I LIKE YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> I HAVEN'T TOLD ANYONE THAT.
>> YOU JUST KEEP ME RIGHT THERE
AND I'LL KEEP YOU, OKAY?
>> I GOT YOU IF YOU GOT ME,
OKAY?
>> I GOT YOU.
>> HEY, WHILE WE'RE OVER HERE BY
OURSELVES I THINK AN ALLIANCE
NEEDS TO STAY RIGHT HERE.
WE'RE THE STRONGEST, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
IF THERE'S ANY WEAK TIES I DON'T
THINK IT SHOULD BE THE THREE OF
US FIRST.
JUST TO LET YOU KNOW SO YOU KNOW
I'M NOT COMING FROM LEFT FIELD
AND TRYING TO VOODOO YOU.
I'VE GRABBED ALLIANCES WITH ALL
OF THEM.
SO IT'S EASY FOR ME TO TAKE ANY
ONE OF THEM IN IF YOU WANT TO.
>> OKAY, I LIKE THIS THREE.
>> I LIKE THIS THREE.
>> I'M NOT DOING THAT FLIP-FLOP
THING.
>> I'M NOT NEITHER, OKAY?
>> THAT'S WHAT I EXPECT.
>> I'M IN.
>> COOL.
>> HEY, YOU GOT EXPERIENCE AND
HE'S A BAR TENDER FROM GEORGIA.
(LAUGHTER)
I'M ALREADY A SUPERSTAR.
MADE ALLIANCES WITH EVERYBODY ON
THE TRIBE AND EVERYBODY SEEMS TO
THINK THAT I'M THEIR ONLY
ALLIANCE.
>> THAT MAKES ME VERY HAPPY.
THAT SAVES MY LIFE.
>> IT'S UP TO ME NOW TO PICK
THEM APART.
WHOEVER I'M READY TO SEND HOME
AFTER THIS FIRST CHALLENGE,
THAT'S THE END OF IT, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN IT'S JUST PECKING ORDER.
>> ZANE CAME UP TO ME AND
RUSSELL AT THE FIRE AND THE
FIRST THING HE SAYS IS "I'VE
ALREADY GOTTEN A ALLIANCE WITH
EVERYBODY."
>> I THINK HE'S BRIGHTER THAN WE
BELIEVE.
>> I'M SURE HE IS.
>> THERE'S A STORY THERE.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING GOING ON.
>> ZANE WALKED UP AND SAYS
"LISTEN, I MADE AN ALLIANCE WITH
EVERYBODY ON THE THIS BEACH."
WELL, NOW I FEEL SPECIAL, THANKS
FOR COMING TO ME LAST.
DENICE IS A THERAPIST IN REAL
LIFE.
SHE'S PRACTICED AT KEEPING HER
EMOTIONS OUT OF SITUATIONS AND
REALLY DRAWING THEM OUT OF
OTHERS AND IF SHE'S A GOOD
PERSON TO HAVE AROUND FOR ME TO
SCHEME WITH.
SO IT COULD END UP BEING AN
ALLIANCE THAT I END UP STAYING
WITH FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
>> HAVE YOU THOUGHT LONG TERM?
>> I MEAN, NOT SUPER LONG TERM
BUT I KNOW THAT I DON'T WANT TO
BE SITTING IN RUSSELL SWAN'S
SHADOW FOR A LONG TIME.
>> NO, NO.
>> AND IT'S GOING TO BE US TWO.
WE COOL?
>> I-- I JUST HAD THIS GUT
INSTINCT ABOUT MALCOLM.
HE'S YOUNG BY WISE AND INSTANTLY
WE JUST CLICKED.
AND IT WAS LIKE WHAT ARE YOU
FEELING?
HERE'S WHAT I'M FEELING.
SO AS LONG AS MY ALLIANCE WITH
MALCOLM HOLDS.
I'M GOOD.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DO THIS, THIS
IS GOING TO BE OUR CELEBRATION.
>> ROOF.
ONCE WE GET THE ROOF WE CAN
ALWAYS GET OUT OF ANYTHING.
I'M NOT COMFORTABLE WITH THE
LEVEL OF PROGRESS SO FAR BECAUSE
WE DON'T HAVE A FIRE WHICH MEANS
WE DON'T HAVE WATER AND IT'S
BEEN RAINING SINCE THE CRACK OF
DAWN.
SO I KNEW I NEEDED TO TAKE A
REAL STRONG LEADERSHIP ROLE HERE
RIGHT NOW AND SAY LET'S GET ON
THIS.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I SHOULD HAVE SAW THAT
COMING.
IT'S JUST A BLISTER.
IT'S NOTHING.
>> TAKE CARE OF THAT, KEEP IT
CLEAN.
WE NEED YOU.
I THINK SKUPIN GIVES 110%
CONSTANTLY BUT BY DOING THAT HE
MISSES THE LITTLE STUFF LIKE A
TWIG OR A BAMBOO SHOOT THAT'S
GOING TO HIT YOU IN THE HEAD.
>> INSIDE OR OUTSIDE.
>> I THINK IT'S JUST A SCRAPE.
IT DOESN'T HURT.
INJURED ON THE SECOND DAY.
>> IT'S MORE UNDERSTANDING WHAT
HAPPENED ON THE OUTBACK AND HIM
FALLING INTO THE FIRE NOW.
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT
INJURIES.
>> THESE ARE LITTLE THINGS.
>> I KNOW BUT LITTLE THINGS CAN
TURN INTO BIG THINGS.
I THINK HE THINKS HE'S SUPERMAN.
SUPERMAN NEEDS TO TAKE A LITTLE
BIT OF A BREAK.
AND MAYBE, YOU KNOW, TAKE THE
MACHETE AWAY FROM HIP.
MAYBE THAT'S HIS KRYPTONITE.
YOU OKAY?
>> I HAVE A CUT ON MY FOOT.
>> COME ON, MIKE!
THAT'S NOT A BABY CUT, EITHER.
>> ANYTHING WE CAN DO TO HELP?
>> NO.
I'M CUT, I GOT RIPPED SKIN.
I-- I CHOPPED MY HEAD OFF.
>> IS THAT FINGER, FOOT, HEAD
NOW?
>> (LAUGHS)
BUT I'M NOT ACCIDENT PRONE, IT'S
THE WAY THAT I GO THROUGH LIFE,
ACT FIRST, THINK SECOND.
NOTHING IS ANYWHERE NEAR AN
ISSUE.
I'M STILL GOOD.
WE DIDN'T HAVE COCONUTS IN THE
OUTBACK.
THIS IS A NEW ADVENTURE FOR ME.
OUCH!
DAMN IT!
>> LET'S GET YOU SOME WATER.
>> IT'S A SMALL CUT.
>> MIKE--
>> LOOK, LOOK.
>> OKAY, LIKE I SAY, EVERYTHING
ON YOU IS A SMALL CUT.
>> EVERYTHING HAS BEEN.
>> MIKE'S A COMPLETES ME.
IT'S NOT FUNNY THAT HE GETS HURT
BUT IT'S FUNNY THAT IT HAPPENS
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
>> I'M ABOUT READY TO BAN YOU
FROM USING THE KNIFE ANYMORE.
>> I MEAN, WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN IN
ANY SITUATIONS WHERE HE CAN
SERIOUSLY GET INJURED BUT, I
MEAN, WE'LL SEE WHEN WE HAVE
FIRE WHAT HAPPENS.
(LAUGHS)
>> WELL, I ALREADY DON'T LIKE
THE SHADY STUFF THAT'S GOING
AROUND WITH JONATHAN.
I MEAN, WE ALL STICK TOGETHER.
WE'RE LIKE A FAMILY.
AND HE'S JUST OFF DOING HIS OWN
THING AND I FEEL LIKE THAT'S NOT
UNITY.
SO HE'S DANGEROUS.
>> I HAVE BEEN LOOKING FOR THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL ALL DAY.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING AT ALL THE
OBVIOUS PLACES THAT I THINK IT
COULD BE.
THERE'S THE TREE WITH THE ARCH.
THERE'S THE TREE IN THE WATER.
NOWHERE.
NOWHERE'SVILLE.
THEN I SAY OF COURSE, IT'S IN
THE CAMP RIGHT NOW.
BURIED IN THE DIRT OR ATTACHED
UNDERNEATH OR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT.
THEN I REMEMBER THE ONE THING
THAT I WAS WAITING FOR US WHEN
WE FIRST HIT THE BEACH WAS A
MACHETE AND A POT WHICH YOU
ALWAYS HAVE, BUT THERE WAS ALSO
THIS BEAUTIFUL BOX WITH A BIG
BAG OF RICE.
IT'S IN THE RICE.
IT HAS TO BE!
HA HA!
FIND IT, FIND THE CLUE!
AN IDOL LAYS IN WAITING
SOMEWHERE NEAR
THE BEACH.
IT COULD BE SALVATION AND IT'S
RIGHT UNDER YOUR NOSE.
THE IDOL IS EITHER IN THE RICE
BUCKET ITSELF OR UNDERNEATH OUR
CAMP.
IT'S THERE, WAITING FOR ME.
BUT I NEED TO FIND THE THING!
TELL US ABOUT THE RICE, LIKE DO
YOU--
>> TWO CUPS OF RICE, ONE CUP OF
WATER.
>> SO TWO COCONUT WATERS AND A--
>> COCONUT RICE.
>> OKAY.
I LOVE RICE; RICE LOVES ME.
THAT LOOKS LIKE I'M GOING TO
NEED THAT MUCH.
I GO TO COOK THE RICE.
THERE'S A PIECE OF PAPER IN
THERE.
I'M LIKE THAT'S THE CLUE!
I'M GOOD!
JUST HAPPENSTANCE!
JUST HERE IS LUCK.
(READING)
>> SO I'M SWIMMING AND I SEE
RUSSELL AS HE'S SHUFFLING WITH
THE FIREWOOD HE'S REACHING IN
HIS POCKET.
>> THAT DUDE IS ON MY CASE.
>> I DON'T TRUST RUSSELL NO
FARTHER THAN I CAN SLING HIM.
THIS IS THE SECOND TIME IN THIS
GAME.
EVERYBODY ELSE IT'S THEIR FIRST
RODEO.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE I'M WORRIED
ABOUT.
>> HAVE YOU HAD A CHANCE TO LOOK
FOR THE IDOL?
>> DUDE, I DON'T EVEN DO THAT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S DEFINITELY
SOMETHING THAT HELPED
TREMENDOUSLY BUT I'M GOING TO
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW, I SEE
SOMEBODY LOOKING FOR THE IDOL
AND I CATCH THEM, TARGET.
>> I POINT BLANK ASKED RUSSELL
"HAVE YOU BEEN LOOKING FOR THE
IDOL?"
"NO, I'M NOT LOOKING FOR THE
IDOL BECAUSE WE'RE TEAMMATES.
IF I SEE ANYBODY LOOKING FOR IT,
I'M VOTING THEM OUT."
HE'S SO CALM AND CHARISMATIC IT
MAKES ME BELIEVE HE'S ALREADY
GOT IT.
>> IF YOU GET IT YOU'RE GOING
NEXT!
BEST BELIEVE THAT.
SO.
>> SO IF WE LOSE FIRST CHALLENGE
WE'LL GET RID OF RUSSELL.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
EACH TRIBE WILL BE DIVIDED INTO
PAIRS.
THE FIRST PAIR WILL BE TIED
TOGETHER.
THEY'LL RACE INTO THE JUNGLE, UP
A CARGO NET WHERE YOU WILL
RELEASE TWO PADDLES.
THE NEXT PAIR WILL USE THOSE
PADDLES TO RACE THEIR BOAT OUT
TO A BUOY.
YOU'LL DIVE DOWN, RELEASE A
CHEST, SWIM IT BACK TO SHORE.
THE FINAL PAIR WILL OPEN THAT
CHEST AND USE THE PIECES INSIDE
TO SOLVE THE PUZZLE.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: THIS IS WHAT IT'S ALL
ABOUT RIGHT HERE.
THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
WITH IMMUNITY YOU ARE SAFE IN
THIS GAME.
WITHOUT IT, YOU ARE IN TROUBLE.
THE SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY.
THE LOSING TRIBE GOES TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY FROM YOUR
TRIBE WILL BE THE FIRST PERSON
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION YOU AREPLAYING FOR
REWARD.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH A
COMPLETE FIRE-MAKING KIT.
(APPLAUSE)
>> YES, INDEED!
>> Jeff: THE SECOND TRIBE TO
FINISH, FLINT.
NOT QUITE AS COMPLETE BUT THIS
WILL HELP YOU GET IT DONE.
LOSING TRIBE, NOTHING, SEE YOU
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BIG STAKES.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO DIVIDE
UP INTO PAIRS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> HOW Y'ALL WANT TO DO THIS?
>> WE'RE RUNNERS.
>> OKAY.
I NEED YOU GUYS TO JUST CALM
DOWN.
>> WHO THINKS YOU SHOULD BE WEAR
WHERE?
>> I THINK YOU GUYS SHOULD DO
THE BOAST.
>> TO ME THE QUESTION IS WHO'S
THE STRONGER PADDLER.
>> I'M TERRIBLE AT PUZZLES.
I'M A PHYSICAL PERSON.
ALL RIGHT?
>> I'M THE SAME WAY.
>> I WANT YOU TWO TO DO THE
PUZZLE.
I KNOW YOU MIGHT BE PANICKING.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO I THINK THAT--
WHY DO PEOPLE WHO ARE--
>> HOLD ON.
JUST BEAR WITH ME.
YOU TWO DO THE PUZZLES, ALL
RIGHT?
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
THE LOSING TRIBE GOES TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
RUSSELL AND ZANE, ARTIS AND R.C.
AND DANA AND KATIE.
>> RUN!
DIG IN!
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> COME ON!
>> THEY'RE AHEAD OF US.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY WONDERING
WHO IS OFF TO A GOOD START.
THE FASTER YOU GET BACK WITH
THOSE PADDLES, THE FASTER YOUR
TRIBE IS IN THE WATER.
>> COME ON, GIRLS!
>> Jeff: WHO WILL BE OUT
FIRST?
(CHEERING).
>> Jeff: R.C. AND ARTIS ARE
FIRST OUT.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL AND DAVE
RIGHT BEHIND!
ZANE DRAGGING!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL LIKE A DRILL
SERGEANT.
>> Jeff: .
>> COME ON ZANE!
>> PULL ME!
PULL ME!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN AND PETE IN
THE WATER.
BRINGING UP THE REAR, A LONG WAY
BEHIND DANA AND KATIE CAL BOW,
PICK IT UP, LADIES.
>> GO, GUYS!
>> Jeff: KATIE AND DANA BACK
WITH THE PADDLES FOR CAL BOW.
JEFF AND CARTER ARE GOING TO DO
PADDLING.
THEY HERE IN THE WATER.
THEY'VE GOT TIME TO MAKE UP.
>> GO, BOYS, GO!
>> Jeff: THERE'S A BIG WIND
PUSHING EVERYBODY TO THE RIGHT.
SKUPIN AND PETE WITH A BIG LEAD!
FOR TANDANG.
NOW THEY'VE GOT TO RELEASE THE
CHEST.
>> TANDANG!
WHAT!
WHOO!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN AND PETE HAVE
THEIR CHEST AND THEY'RE HEADING
BACK!
>> ATTA BOY!
>> Jeff: JEFF AND CARTER
MAKING UP GROUND FOR CAL BOW.
>> JEFF AND CARTER!
LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: CAL BOW HAS TAKEN
OVER T LEAD OVER MATSING.
>> YEAH!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: CARTER AND JEFF MADE
UP A LOT OF TIME FOR KALABAW.
>> KEEP PADDLING!
JEFF AND CARTER HAVE THE CHAS
FOR KALABAW.
MALCOLM AND DENICE IN THE WATER
FOR MATSING!
COME ON!
LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: MATSING HAS THEIR
CHEST UP!
>> MATSING!
>> Jeff: ALL THREE TRIBES ARE
HEADING BACK.
A BIG LEAD FOR TANDANG!
>> COME ON, TANDANG, YOU GOT
THIS!
>> Jeff: ONCE YOU CROSS THIS,
EVERYBODY COME HELP.
COME ON DOWN!
ALL SIX OF YOU HAVE TO GET THIS
UP.
>> GRAB IT!
>> Jeff: THE CHEST WEIGHS A
TON.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> Jeff: JEFF AND CARTER
ALMOST BACK TO SHORE.
MALCOLM AND DENICE STRUGGLING IN
THE WATER.
>> COME ON, GUYS, COME ON, GUYS.
YOU GOT ANYTHING LEFT IN YOU?
THIS IS WHERE WE'RE GOING TO
CATCH UP.
>> Jeff: COME ON DOWN!
THE REST OF THE KALABAW TRIBE
CAN HELP OUT.
THIS CHEST WEIGHS A LOT.
THERE YOU GO.
PUZZLE MAKERS TAKE OVER!
NOTHING EASY ABOUT THIS
CHALLENGE.
>> YOU CAN DO IT!
MATSING IS BACK WITH THEIR
CHEST.
EVERYBODY COME DOWN AND HELP!
YOU GUYS ARE STILL IN THIS.
>> WE'RE THERE!
>> Jeff: TANDANG HAS HAD A
NICE LEAD.
KALABAW, THOUGH, RIGHT IN THIS.
SOON MATSING WILL BE IN HERE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO FINISH LAST.
LAST MEANS TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THERE YOU GO.
PUZZLE MAKERS, TAKE OVER.
ROXANNE AND ANGIE WORKING ON IT
FOR MATSING.
PENNER AND DAWSON WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE FOR KALABAW.
ABI-MARIA ABI-MARIA AND LISA
WORKING ON IT FOR TANDANG.
DOING A NICE JOB TO KEEP THEIR
LEAD.
>> YES, GIRL!
>> Jeff: BIG REWARD THAT GOES
ALONG WITH IMMUNITY.
BUT THE MAIN THING YOU WANT IS
TO FINISH FIRST OR FINISH SECOND
BUT DON'T FINISH LAST.
>> OKAY!
>> TURN IT AROUND.
>> Jeff: PENNER TRYING TO
CATCH FOR KALABAW.
>> RIGHT THERE!
>> Jeff: RUSSELL DESPERATELY
TRYING TO CATCH UP.
PANIC IS NOT YOUR FRIEND.
FOCUS IS THE KEY.
TANDANG CONTINUES TO EXTEND
THEIR LEAD.
KALABAW, THOUGH, RIGHT BEHIND
AND MATSING WITH A LOT OF TIME
TO MAKE UP.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: KALABAW AND TANDANG
DEAD EVEN BOTH WITH THREE PIECES
LEFT.
>> KEEP GOING!
DON'T LOOK!
>> Jeff: MATSING FALLING
FURTHER AND FURTHER BEHIND.
>> TURN IT AROUND!
>> Jeff: ANOTHER PIECE FOR
KALABAW!
NOW WE'VE GOT A RACE FOR FIRST.
LEE IS WITH ANOTHER PIECE!
TWO PIECES LEFT.
PEN WE ARE ANOTHER PIECE FOR
KALABAW.
LISA VERY CLOSE FOR TANDANG!
CAN SHE GET THE TOP ON?
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
KALABAW FIRST TO FINISH.
WE'RE STILL GOING FOR SECOND.
AND LISA DOES IT.
TANDANG SURVIVES WINNING
IMMUNITY AND REWARD AS WELL.
MATSING HEADING TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> I TOLD YOU, I'M NOT GOOD AT
PUZZLES.
>> Jeff: KALABAW, HUGE
COME-FROM-BEHIND VICTORY.
GET YOUR REWARD.
IMMUNITY AND A FIRE-MAKING KIT.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM YOUR
TRIBE.
TANDANG, NOT QUITE AS BIG A
REWARD BUT YOU GOT WHAT YOU
NEEDED: IMMUNITY AND FLINT TO GO
ALONG WITH IT.
GOOD WORK.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR TANDANG.
MATSING, WHAT HAPPENED RUSSELL?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, JEFF, ALL I
CAN SAY IS AT THE END OF THE DAY
I MADE THE DECISION ON WHO WAS
GOING TO DO WHAT SO I CARRY SOME
OF THAT WATER.
IT'S JUST-- WE ALL HAVE TO CLICK
NEXT TIME.
AND THAT'S THE BEAUTY, JEFF.
THERE ALWAYS IS A NEXT TIME.
>> Jeff: THERE'S A NEXT TIME
FOR FIVE OF YOU.
NOT A NEXT TIME FOR ALL SIX OF
YOU.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT, SOMEBODY
FROM YOUR TRIBE WILL BE THE
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
THAT OUT.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF; HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> Jeff: .
>> RUSSELL TOOK OVER AND DIDN'T
LISTEN TO A SINGLE WORD ANYBODY
SAID SO I GET TO GO SEE TRIBAL
ON NIGHT THREE.
>> NOW YOU KNOW HOW THIS GOES.
YOU SEE THESE CHALLENGES ARE
BRUTAL.
BUT I'VE PLAYED THIS GAME BEFORE
AND I'M TELLING YOU YOU HAVE TO
DIG SO DEEP IN YOURSELF.
>> CAN I SPEAK BEFORE-- AND I'D
LIKE TO TALK TO THE WHOLE TRIBE,
ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT THIS
GAME WHERE YOU JUST HAVE TO-- I
MEAN, YOU'VE GOT TO PULL THE
FIRE OUT OF YOUR STOMACH AND
DECIDE THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO THROW DOWN.
AND YOU HAD TO PULL ME.
I THREW MYSELF ON TOP-- I MEAN,
THREE DAYS IN, BROTHER.
I AIN'T BUILT FOR IT.
>> AS I'M KIND OF FINISHING THE
PEP TALK, ZANE BASICALLY CUTS ME
OFF AND THE GUY THROWS HIMSELF
UNDER THE BUS.
>> MY LEGS CRAMPED SO HARD THAT
I SAT, YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
Y'ALL DIDN'T.
SO I DON'T FEEL LIKE THAT IT'S A
CHOICE.
>> WHAT IT DID WAS IT MADE THE
DECISION PRETTY DAMN EASY IN
TERMS OF WHO'S GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> I LOVE THIS GAME AND I LOVE
IT FOR KNOWING HOW POWERFUL IT
IS, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
BUT I DESERVE-- I DESERVE TO GO.
MY WHOLE REASON WHY I'M THROWING
MY NECK ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK IS
TO ESTABLISH WHAT I'M RUNNING
AGAINST.
THIS WHOLE RUSE THAT I JUST
THREW ON WAS JUST TO FILL OUT MY
TRIBE EXACTLY HOW I NEED TO WORK
THINGS.
IT'S GOING TO BE WORSE AND WORSE
AND WORSE.
SO HOPEFULLY EVERYBODY LOVES ME
TO THE POINT TO WHERE THEY WOULD
RATHER HAVE ME AS A HINDRANCE
THAN TO KEEP RUSSELL.
I TOOK MY SHOT, I'M PLAYING
CHESS THE BEST WAY I KNOW HOW
AND HOPEFULLY I'M GOING TO KING
ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU TWO, I THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE ZANE.
ALL RIGHT?
SO YOU GUYS ARE GOOD?
AND-- YOU KNOW, ALL I CAN SAY IS
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR," DIG DEEP,
YOU GUYS GOT IT IN YOU.
>> I'M FORMER MISS UTAH TEEN.
I'M A VERY, VERY COMPETITIVE
PERSON.
I NEVER LIKE TO LOSE.
I'M SO ANNOYED BECAUSE RUSSELL
WANTS EVERYONE TO THINK THAT
HE'S NOT THE LEADER.
HE'S LIKE "I'M NOT THE LEADER,
GUYS."
BUT HE MAKES THOSE CALLS LIKE IN
THE CHALLENGES.
A LEADER WOULD LISTEN TO HIS
TRIBE AND REALLY TAKE INTO
CONSIDERATION WHAT THEIR
STRENGTHS AND WEAKNESSES ARE.
I'M PISSED.
I'M JUST SO BUMMED.
I SAID I'M NOT GOOD AT PUZZLES,
HE PUTS ME AT PUZZLES BECAUSE
HE'S NOT GOOD AT PUZZLES.
>> I DIDN'T LIKE THAT TACK
TAKE--
>> HE'S LIKE I'M NOT GOOD AT
PUZZLES, YOU DO PUZZLES.
I'M NOT GOOD AT PUZZLES, EITHER.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
IF WE HAVE TO VOTE ZANE OUT I
WOULD IF IT WOULD GET ME FURTHER
IN THE GAME BUT I WOULD LIKE TO
SEE RUSSELL GONE BECAUSE I LIKE
ZANE.
HE IS SO FUNNY.
HE'S JUST LIKE-- HE'S A GOOD
GENUINE PERSON AND I WOULD LIKE
TO SEE HIM AROUND.
I KNOW HE'S NOT THAT STRONG IN
CHALLENGES BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO
SEE HIM GIVE UP.
HOW COULD YOU GIVE UP?
>> I'M NOT GIVING UP.
>> YOU'RE TELLING PEOPLE TO VOTE
FOR YOU.
>> LOGISTICALLY HE HAD TO
LITERALLY PULL ME ACROSS THE
LINE.
>> ME AND ROXANNE WANTED TO RUN
AND GUESS WHAT?
HE SAID NO.
IT WAS HIM, NOT YOU.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO VOTE FOR?
>> I MEAN--
>> YOU HAVE TO VOTE FOR RUSSELL.
>> IT'S UP TO Y'ALL, MAN.
I AIN'T GIVING UP.
I'M HERE FOR YOU, YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN?
>> STICK WITH IT.
DON'T GO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ANGIE WAS LIKE "PLEASE DON'T GO
HOME.
LET'S BLIND SIDE RUSS."
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME,
BECAUSE WE NEED YOU.
WE NEED SOME LAUGHTER.
>> YOU AIN'T NEVER SEEN A MOVE
LIKE THIS IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
>> ARE YOU FOR SURE TOSSING IN
THE TOWEL, KID?
YOU'RE NOT TOSSING IN THE TOWEL
BUT-- THAT LOOK IN YOUR EYE
SCARES ME.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT.
>> ARE YOU BLIND SIDING?
>> I MEAN-- IF YOU WANT TO GO
HOME, I'LL SEND YOU HOME BUT,
LIKE, THERE'S SO MANY DIFFERENT
WAYS THE GAME COULD GO.
>> MALCOLM CAME TO ME AND BEGGED
ME TO STAY.
NOW THE ONLY THING I HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT NOW IS IF RUSS
ACTUALLY HAS THE IDOL.
I GIVE YOU 100% THAT HE DOES
HAVE THE IDOL.
>> ZANE WAS ALREADY GOING HOME
BY HIS OWN FREE WILL BUT THE
THING IS WE THINK RUSSELL HAS AN
IDOL.
THE SKETCHIEST PART IS THAT THE
INFORMATION COMES FROM ZANE OF
ALL PEOPLE THAT RUSSELL HAS AN
IDOL.
BUT IF WE VOTE OUT RUSSELL WE'RE
OBVIOUSLY DOWN MULL WISE THREE
DAYS IN.
I THINK ZANE AT ONE POINT ASKED
RUSSELL TO DRAG HIM THROUGH THE
COURSE.
SO QUITE LITERALLY HE'S THE ONE
WEIGHING THE TRIBE DOWN.
HAVE YOU TALKED TO ZANE ABOUT
THE IDOL AT ALL?
>> NO.
>> WE'RE 95% SURE RUSSELL HAD
IT.
>> DAMN IT!
RIGHT NOW THERE'S A FEELING THAT
RUSSELL HAS MAYBE FOUND AN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND SO ZANE MIGHT
HAVE A SHOT TO STAY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, NOTHING AGAINST
ZANE BUT THIS IS NOT THE POINT
IN THE GAME WHERE YOU CAN HAVE
WEAK PLAYERS.
GOD, IT SUCK HAVING TO MAKE THIS
DECISION.
>> OH, MAN.
I DO NOT WANT TO DO THIS.
>> NO.
LET ME TELL YOU, DUDE, THEY
SUCK.
>> I THINK I'M OKAY TONIGHT.
BUT I ACTUALLY MADE MY FIRST
MISTAKE TODAY.
I JUST CLICKED INTO THIS KIND OF
CHIEF MODE, IF YOU WILL, AND
THOUGHT I HAVE TO MAKE THIS
CALL.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO.
THIS IS NOT ABOUT LEADERSHIP.
LEADERSHIP KILLS, DUDE, AND I
WENT RIGHT BACK INTO THE OLD
MODE.
YOU NEVER KNOW WITH THIS GAME.
THESE PEOPLE COULD VOTE ME OUT
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH, GRAB A TORCH, APPROACH
THE FLAME AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE FIRE YOU ARE
STILL IN THIS GAME AND WHEN YOUR
FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE YOU AND
THAT IS GOING TO BE THE CASE FOR
ONE OF YOU TONIGHT.
ONLY THREE DAYS IN, ZANE, AND
SOMEBODY'S GOING HOME.
>> IT'S A SAD THING, JEFF.
BUT IT'S THE WAY OF "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: DENICE, WHAT DO YOU
THINK ABOUT HAVING RETURNING
PLAYERS?
>> YOU KNOW, QUITE HONESTLY I
WAS MIXED AT FIRST BECAUSE I
WANTED IT TO BE A REALLY PURE
GAME KIND OF IN THE SENSE OF
JUST THIS BEING OUR GAME.
BUT IT'S ALREADY BEEN, YOU KNOW,
AN ASSET TO HAVE SOMEBODY REALLY
GIVING US TIPS ON HOW TO DO THIS
OR HOW TO SAVE A FIRE THROUGH
THREE DAYS OF RAIN.
SO IT DEFINITELY CHANGES THE
GAME PLAY.
BUT IN THIS RAIN IT'S A GIFT.
>> Jeff: ZANE, IT'S KIND OF A
TRICKY DILEMMA, ISN'T IT?
YOU HAVE SOMEBODY WHO CAN BRING
SOMETHING YOU NEED, EXPERIENCE.
BUT GOING IN THEY'RE A BETTER
PLAYER THAN YOU.
>> OFF THE TOP THEY ARE BETTER
THAN YOU ARE.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE AN ONION, MAN.
MORE LAYERS YOU PEEL BACK, THE
MORE YOU START TO CRY.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT HAPPENS
AND--
>> Jeff: OKAY, YOU LOST ME.
(LAUGHTER)
>> I WAS NERVOUS--
>> Jeff: WAIT, WAIT.
GO BACK TO THE ONION.
>> YOU KNOW, AT FIRST LIKE YOU
GET SOMETHING OUT OF IT.
THEN YOU GET A LITTLE BIT MORE
OUT OF IT THEN YOU REALIZE
YOU'RE GETTING TOO MUCH OUT OF
IT.
SO THE MORE LAYERS YOU PEEL, THE
MORE YOU CRY, MAN.
THIS GUY IS A KILLER ATHLETE.
HE ALREADY KNOWS ABOUT FIRE AND
WATER AND SHELTER.
LIKE I SAID-- THE MORE YOU PEEL
BACK, THE MORE YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW MUCH OF A BETTER PLAYER
YOU'RE COMING AGAINST RATHER
THAN BEING ON EQUAL GROUND.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
SO NOW THAT I'M CAUGHT UP THERE,
RUSSELL, DOES THAT SOUND LIKE "I
LOVE WHAT YOU'VE TAUGHT US BUT
MAN YOU'RE TOO GOOD OF A PLAYER
AND YOU'RE GOING"?
>> YEAH, THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT
SOUNDS LIKE.
EVEN WITH THIS ONION THING I
THINK TODAY I KIND OF BLEW IT
BECAUSE INSTEAD OF BEING 2.0 AND
JUST BEING PART OF A GROUP I
WENT BACK TO 1.0, THAT DICTATOR.
AND I MADE A HUGE MISTAKE.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, DID YOU PICK
UP ON RUSSELL BECOMES A
DICTATOR, AS HE SAYS?
>> HE CAME ON A LITTLE STRONG
PRE-CHALLENGE TODAY.
>> AND I'M--
>> AND, WE ALL-- IT'S ON THE
TABLE, WE ALL KNOW.
>> IT WAS WRONG.
BUT I WOULDN'T BE COMPLETELY
SHOCKED IF I WAS VOTED OUT
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: HOW DISAPPOINTED
WOULD YOU BE?
>> I MEAN, THE FIRST TIME I
PLAYED I GOT CARRIED OUT ON MY
BACK.
I GET BLESSED WITH A SECOND
OPPORTUNITY TO PLAY AGAIN AND I
GO OUT FIRST.
THAT WOULD JUST BE A DAGGER IN
THE HEART.
>> Jeff: ROXY, DID HE COME ON
A LITTLE STRONG?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I FEEL LIKE OUT OF NOWHERE HE'S
JUST LIKE "NO, WHOA.
IT'S GOING TO BE THIS, THIS, AND
THIS."
AND I HAVE MILITARY BACKGROUND
SO I JUST WENT RIGHT INTO MY
GEAR WHICH IS YOU ARE SUPERIOR
TO ME, THAT IS HOW YOU'RE ACTING
RIGHT NOW, I'M GOING TO TAKE
DIRECTION AND FOLLOW DIRECTIONS.
>> Jeff: ANGIE, DO YOU AGREE
WITH THAT?
>> YES.
YOU KNOW, I RAN TRACK IN HIGH
SCHOOL, I ASKED IF I COULD RUN
BUT NOPE BECAUSE HE DIDN'T WANT
TO DO THE PUZZLE AND HE TOLD ME
IF WE LOSE IT'S YOUR FAULT.
YEAH, THAT'S EXACTLY--
>> I DON'T THINK THAT WAS
EXACTLY WHAT I SAID.
>> Jeff: ANGIE'S PRETTY SURE
IT WAS EXACTLY.
>> WELL, THE BOTTOM LINE IS SHE
IS ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I WENT INTO DICTATOR MODE AND IT
WAS LIKE NOPE, THIS IS WHAT
WE'RE DOING.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HOPEFULLY THIS DAY DOESN'T
BESPEAK FOR THE OTHER TWO DAYS.
ESPECIALLY WHEN I KNOW I HAVE SO
MUCH MORE TO GIVE GIVE AND I
HOPE I GET THAT OPPORTUNITY.
>> Jeff: ZANE, HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT THE LEG YOU WERE ASSIGNED
TO DO?
>> WELL, I QUIT SMOKING THE DAY
OF COMING HERE.
AND I MADE SURE I LET THE WHOLE
TRIBE KNOW THAT, YOU KNOW,
RUNNING AIN'T THE DEAL.
I'M GETTING BACK BUT I AIN'T GOT
BACK, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I KNOW IT'S MY FAULT, I'M A
DUMMY.
I SHOULD HAVE PUT A LITTLE MORE
FORETHOUGHT INTO THAT.
BUT IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> Jeff: REGARDLESS WHO PUT
YOU IN THAT POSITION, IS THERE
RESPONSIBILITY, DENICE, HOW YOU
PERFORM IN A CHALLENGE?
>> I MEAN, I-- ABSOLUTELY.
I COULD SAY I WAS A STRONG
SWIMMER AND I GOT OUT THERE AND
I'M PUSHING A 200 POUND CHEST
AND I SUCKED, SURE, THEY COULD
POINT THAT AT ME.
OR YOU CAN TURN THAT AROUND AND
GO "OR WAS THAT OUR LEADERSHIP?
" IT'S PART OF THE GAME.
>> Jeff: ZANE?
>> WHEN I GOT BACK TO CAMP I
TOLD EVERYBODY SEND ME HOME IF
YOU WANT TO, I UNDERSTAND THE
RUNNING WAS NOT MY DEAL.
I WOULD RATHER STEP OUT OF YOUR
WAY THAN THE HOLD YOU UP.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL, YOU'RE OFF
THE BOX.
>> IT SOUNDS CONVENIENT BUT, YOU
KNOW, JEFF, I'VE BEEN TO THIS
DANCE BEFORE AND YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT CONVERSATIONS HAVE TAKEN
PLACE FROM THAT TIME TO THAT HE
MADE THAT PRONOUNCEMENT TO THIS
TIME NOW.
I KNOW THAT SOMETIMES STUFF CAN
BE CODED, IT CAN CUT ALL KINDS
OF DIFFERENT E WAYS.
>> Jeff: WHAT ODDS DO YOU GIVE
YOURSELF RIGHT NOW THAT YOU'RE
HERE AFTER THIS VOTE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, JEFF.
BUT I'M READY TO BE HERE.
LET'S BE CLEAR.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MALCOLM, YOU'RE UP.
>> ZANE, I'M NOT READY TO GO
HOME YET.
I WISH YOU LOTS OF LUCK, MAN.
>> IF YOU AIN'T FIRST, YOU'RE
LAST.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ZANE.
RUSS.
ZANE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ZANE, ONE
VOTE RUSS.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES," ZANE.
THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU'VE GOT TO
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ZANE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> SON OF A BITCH!
>> Jeff: WELL, THE GOOD NEWS
IS YOU SURVIVED YOUR FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE BAD NEWS IS YOU'RE ALREADY
DOWN TO FIVE PEOPLE LEFT.
ONE MORE THING.
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, YOU NOW HAVE FIRE IN
THE FORM OF FLINT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.