>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR" --
>> I NEVER FELT THAT ANY OF YOU
FELT THAT WAY ABOUT ME.
>> Jeff: ABI FINALLY FOUND OUT
THAT SHE WAS UNIVERSALLY
DESPISED.
>> SHE CONTINUES THE REIN OF
NEGATIVE, GRUMPY ABI.
>> Jeff: BUT IN ORDER TO SAVE
HERSELF SHE BOUGHT AN ADVANTAGE
AT THE AUCTION.
>> 500.
>> Jeff: SOLD TO ABI FOR $500.
>> MOVE DIRECTLY TO THE FINAL
ROUND IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: SHE USED THAT
ADVANTAGE AS PART OF A CRAZY
SCHEME.
>> THERE IS A FOURTH IDOL, BABY.
>> Jeff: TO MAKE PEOPLE THINK
SHE HAD A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> THEY ASKED FOR THIS.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR ME TO LIE.
I'M GOING TO OUTPLAY THEM.
>> Jeff: NONE OF THAT MATTERED
WHEN SHE WON IMMUNITY.
ABI WINS IMMUNITY!
>> YES!
>> Jeff: SAFE AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL!
AT TRIBAL, IT WAS CLEAR THERE
WAS A MAJORITY OF ALLIANCE OF
MALCOLM, DENICE, AND LISA AND
SKUPIN.
>> I BELIEVE DENICE AND MALCOLM
SHOOK HAND AND GAVE THEIR WORDS
TO SKUPIN AND LISA.
>> Jeff: BUT PENNER TRIED TO
CONVINCE LISA IT WAS A BAD IDEA.
>> IF YOU VOTE ME OUT TONIGHT
YOU WILL GIVE THE MILLION
DOLLARS TO ONE OF THESE TWO
PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: TRUE TO FORM, LISA
KEPT HER WORD AND VOTED OUT
PENNER.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SIX ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> CRAZY GAME.
IT'S CLEAR TO ME THAT LISA AND
DENICE, MALCOLM AND SKUPIN HAVE
A FOURSOME ALLIANCE GOING ON.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT REALLY THINKING ABOUT IT
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: BETWEEN ME AND
CARTER, WHO ARE THEY GOING TO
TAKE?
A GUY FROM KANSAS OR A GIRL FROM
BRAZIL THAT THEY HAVE ISSUES
WITH BECAUSE SHE'S TOO HONEST?
>> IF YOU GOT THE IMMUNITY IDOL,
YOU'LL BE GOING FARTHER IN THIS
GAME.
>> IT'S NOT IF, I DO.
(LAUGHS)
THERE IS NO IF.
THERE IS I DO.
I'M GOING TO CONTINUE TO BLUFF I
HAVE THAT THE FOURTH HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE FOR ME.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> KIND OF YOU'VE TAKEN A COUPLE
PUNCHES AND YOU'RE FEELING KIND
OF DIZZY.
YOUR HEAD'S KIND OF SPINNING,
KIND OF CONFUSED, KIND OF .
WELL, THAT WAS THE GOAL OF
SOMEBODY TONIGHT, TO MAKE YOU
DOUBT YOURSELF AND TRY TO GET
YOU TO DO SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS A VERY
TOUGH DECISION.
I THINK PENNER IS CORRECT.
I DO THINK MALCOLM IS PLAYING A
BRILLIANT GAME.
BECAUSE IT'S STRATEGIC BUT
LIKABLE, UNDERDOG, GOOD AT
CHALLENGES.
ALL AROUND REALLY GREAT GAME.
>> HEY, LISA?
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE YOU STOOD UP FOR
YOURSELF.
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T BACK DOWN.
>> THANK YOU.
GOING TO THE END WITH MALCOLM
AND DENICE IS NOT A GREAT
STRATEGY.
BUT BETRAYING THAT TRUST IS --
OPPOSES WHO I AM.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU WILL BE PAIRED UP WITH A
LOVED ONE.
>> OH, MY GOD GOSH!
OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, HERE'S YOUR
SON, ALSO NAMED MICHAEL SKUPIN.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
OH, MY GOSH!
LET ME SEE YOU!
I CAN STILL PICK YOU UP!
MY NUMBER ONE.
MY NUMBER ONE!
>> I'M GOING TO CRY.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR FAMILY.
I GUESS THIS IS YOUR OLDEST
SINCE YOU NAMED YOUR SON MICHAEL
SKUPIN.
>> THERE'S NO DESCRIPTION FOR
HIM.
HE'S THE BEST HUMAN BEING I
KNOW.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> I LEARNED EVERYTHING FROM
HIM.
FOR 12 YEARS IT'S "DAD, LET'S DO
IT TOGETHER!"
HE MET YOU 12 YEARS AGO AND HE
PROBABLY DOESN'T EVEN REMEMBER,
THAT'S PROBST!
>> I KNOW!
I WAS FREAKING OUT!
>> Jeff: CARTER, WHO WOULD YOU
LIKE TO SEE RIGHT NOW?
>> MY MOM.
>> Jeff: CARTER, HERE'S YOU
MOM.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
(APPLAUSE)
OH, MY GOSH!
THIS NEVER HAPPENS!
>> Jeff: WHAT NEVER HAPPENS?
>> I NEVER BREAK DOWN LIKE THIS!
THIS IS JUST -- OH!
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> Jeff: DENICE?
HERE'S YOUR MAN BRAD.
>> WHERE'S HE AT?
WHERE'S HE AT?
(SCREAMS)
I'M SNOTTY AND STICKY.
>> OH, THAT'S SO CUTE!
>> CAN I BORROW YOUR SHIRT?
>> Jeff: BRAD, YOU'RE NOW A
SURVIVOR, YOU HAVE SNOT ON YOUR
SHIRT.
STEP ONE IN THE GAME.
>> THIS IS THE GUY WHO TRULY CAN
MAKE ME LAUGH, CAN CALM ME --
CALL ME ON MY WHATEVER IT IS AND
WAKE UP THE NEXT MORNING AND
IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> SHE HAS SO MUCH STRENGTH, SO
MUCH LOVE ALL IN THIS TIGHT,
TINY LITTLE PACKAGE.
IT'S SO MUCH MORE THAN PEOPLE
CAN EVER EVEN KNOW.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JOIN THE
OTHERS.
YOU CAN CARRY HER OVER.
(APPLAUSE)
LISA, HERE'S YOUR BROTHER
JUSTICE.
>> SISTER!
SISTER!
(SOBBING)
>> Jeff: GOT TO SAY, LISA, I
HAVE SEEN SOME PRETTY POWERFUL
MOMENTS INVOLVING LOVED ONES BUT
THIS MIGHT BE AT THE TOP.
>> I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER
NEEDED ANY PERSON MORE IN MY
LIFE IN THIS MOMENT.
AND IF I COULD PICK ANY PERSON
IT WOULD BE MY BABY BROTHER.
I HAVEN'T EVEN LOOKED AT YOU.
>> YOU'RE DOING IT.
>> ISN'T HE BEAUTIFUL!
>> Jeff: GOOD LOOKING KID.
ABI, YOU'VE HAD A TOUGH JOURNEY
OF LATE.
IT WOULD BE NICE TO HAVE A
LITTLE LOVE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WHO BETTER THAN YOUR
MOM.
>> MY MOM!
>> Jeff: HERE'S YOUR MOM VEER
HAVE.
>> Jeff: TRANSLATE FOR US.
>> SHE'S JUST HAPPY TO SEE ME
BUT SHE'S VERY CONFUSED WITH
EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: WILL, IT'S QUITE A
JOURNEY TO GET HERE.
>> IT WAS A JOURNEY TO GET HERE.
SHE DOESN'T SPEAK ENGLISH
CLEARLY SO SHE'S JUST VERY
CONFUSED.
>> Jeff: WELL, LET HER KNOW
WE'RE SO HAPPY SHE'S HERE.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: .
>> SHE SAYS SHE'S HAPPY TO BE
HERE.
>> Jeff: GREAT, JOIN THE
OTHERS.
NOW THAT EVERYBODY'S HAD THEIR
LOVE --
>> WAIT, JEFF, YOU MADE A
MISTAKE.
>> Jeff: OH, I WOULDN'T LEAVE
YOU OUT, MALCOLM.
HERE'S YOUR BROTHER MILES.
(APPLAUSE)
>> I'M LIGHT, I'M LIGHT!
>> Jeff: HE WAS GOING TO KNOCK
YOU OVER.
>> DO YOU SEE THIS?
>> I LOOK SO GOOD WITH MY SHIRT
OFF NOW YOU WON'T BELIEVE.
I'M TAKING THAT HEAD BAND, TOO.
>> HE LOOKS LIKE A COLONEL, I'M
LIKE SOME SHIP IN THE 1700s --
(LAUGHS)
WHAT'S UP?
>> Jeff: I KNOW MALCOLM'S A
FAN.
WERE YOU A FAN?
>> WE WATCHED EVERY EPISODE.
>> .
>> WE WEREN'T ALLOWED TO WATCH
T.V. DURING THE WEEK UNLESS IT
WAS YOU.
>> I'M ALWAYS FOLLOWING IN HIS
FOOTSTEPS.
I'M ALWAYS --
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GETTING A
LITTLE BROTHER EMOTION ON US.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: IT'S OKAY, MAN,
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE.
>> YEAH, I FOLLOW IN HIS
FOOTSTEPS AND NOW I'M OUT DOING
HIS OWN THING SO I'M GOING TO
LET HIM BE ON "SURVIVOR" AND I'M
SURE HE'S DOING GREAT.
HE'S HERE.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET TO TODAY'S
CHALLENGE.
ON MY GO EACH SURVIVOR WILL TOSS
A MUDDY BAG TO THEIR LOVED ONE.
THE LOVED ONE MUST CATCH THE BAG
AND THEN USE IT TO KNOCK DOWN A
BAMBOO TARGET.
FIRST TEAM TO KNOCK DOWN ALL
FIVE OF THEIR TARGETS WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES, EVERYBODY!
>> Jeff: THE WINNING SURVIVOR
WILL GET TO TAKE THEIR LOVED ONE
BACK TO CAMP.
YOU WILL SPEND THE AFTERNOON AND
THE NIGHT.
LOVED ONES, ARE YOU READY TO
PARTICIPATE IN A "SURVIVOR"
CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: WE'RE GOING TO DRAW
FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> RUN FASTER, DON'T WAIT TO
LOOK.
>> Jeff: MILES KNOCKS ONE OFF
FOR MALCOLM'S TEAM.
BRAD KNOCKS ONE DOWN FOR
DENICE'S TEAM.
NICE, MOM!
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: BIANCA KNOCKS A
SECOND ONE DOWN FOR CARTER'S
TEAM.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: DENICE HAS THREE
LEFT.
>> GOT ONE!
>> Jeff: JUSTICE KNOCKS A
SECOND ONE DOWN.
BRAD MISS.
LISA HAS TWO LEFT.
>> UGH!
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: CARTER HAS TWO LEFT.
MALCOLM HAS TWO LEFT.
MICHAEL SKUPIN KNOCKS ONE DOWN.
>> NICE, ONE MORE, MOM!
>> Jeff: CARTER DOWN TO ONE!
>> GOOD PACE!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM DOWN TO ONE
WITH MILES.
SKUPIN DOWN TO ONE NOW!
>> COME ON, MOM!
>> YOU'RE ALL OVER IT.
COME ON!
>> YES!
OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM AND MILES WIN
REWARD!
(SCREAMING)
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU JUST DID
THAT!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MALCOLM,
MILES, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> CONGRATS, YOU GUYS.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: SO HERE'S WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU AND YOUR BROTHER WILL GO
BACK TO CAMP.
HE'LL SPEND THE AFTERNOON AND
NIGHT.
ARE YOU READY FOR THAT?
PICK ONE OTHER SURVIVOR TO BRING
THEIR LOVED ONE TO JOIN YOU.
>> OH, MALCOLM --
>> I CAN'T LOOK UP.
I CAN'T LOOK ANY OF YOU IN THE
EYE.
UM --
>> BROTHER/SISTER LOVE.
>> JUST BECAUSE OF THE PAST FEW
DAYS HAVE GONE AND HOW MUCH
TROUBLE SOMEBODY IS HAVING OUT
HERE, LISA.
>> YES!
YES!
>> CAN I RUN OVER AND HUG YOU?
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU!
BROTHER/SISTER LOVE.
>> I HAD TO.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, ASK FOR
ANOTHER.
>> CAN I HAVE ANOTHER?
>> YOU ASKED FOR ANOTHER.
ABSOLUTELY.
ONE MORE SURVIVOR AND ANOTHER
WILL JOIN YOU.
>> PLEASE, MALCOLM.
PLEASE.
>> Jeff: THIS WILL BE IT.
>> I'M SORRY, GUYS, SKUPIN.
>> COME WITH ME, BUDDY!
>> DON'T HURT ME, GUYS, DON'T
HURT ME.
>> I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CARTER,
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO SAY
GOOD-BYE TO YOUR MOM.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> BE CAREFUL.
I LOVE YOU.
>> WE LOVE YOUR WIFE, BRAD,
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF HER.
WE PROMISE.
>> BYE, MOM.
>> Jeff: HECK OF A GUY.
ONE HECK OF A GUY.
>> I'LL TURN AROUND THIS GAME
FOR YOU, MOM.
>> ONE HECK OF A GUY.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE ALL GOING BACK
TO CAMP TOGETHER.
ENJOY THE "SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE,
IT IS A ONCE IN A LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY TO SHARE THIS WITH
THE PEOPLE WHO MEAN SO MUCH TO
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> I DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME.
YOU ONLY HAVE MOMENTS TO MAKE
THIS DECISION AND I'M REWARDING
LISA AND SKUPIN FOR STICKING
WITH ME AND DENICE AT THE LAST
TRIBAL AND THROUGH THE PAST FEW
VOTES.
THOSE ARE MY ALLIES.
I NEED TO TAKE CARE OF THEM AND
KEEP THEM CLOSE.
>> WOW!
>> WELCOME TO OUR HUMBLE ABODE.
>> DANGRAYNE.
HOW MANY DAYS HAS THIS BEEN?
>> WE'RE ON DAY 31.
THAT'S OUR CALENDAR.
>> DAY 31!
WHOA MY GOSH YOU'RE SO -- SO
CLOSE!
>> JUSTICE AND I HAVE ALWAYS HAD
A VERY CLOSE RELATIONSHIP.
HE IS TRULY INCREDIBLE.
HE'S 20 YEARS YOUNGER THAN ME
BUT WITHIN HIM IS SO MUCH
MATURITY AND LIFE AND
LIFE-GIVING SPIRIT.
>> THIS IS 39 DAYS.
IT'S GONE BUY IN A BLINK, I
HAVEN'T REALLY MISSED MALCOLM.
(LAUGHTER)
>> MILES, MY LITTLE BROTHER
TURNED 21 YEARS OLD A MONTH AGO.
HE'S A KNUCKLEHEAD IN A REALLY
NICE -- LIKE A NICE WAY.
HE'S JUST KIND OF A CLOWN.
>> I WAS SITTING THERE WITH MY
SHIRT UP TOUCHING MY NIP UNTIL
THIS MIDDLE OF THIS BAR.
>> HE'S ALWAYS AROUND TRYING TO
GET A LAUGH.
HE WANTS TO BE THE CENTER OF
ATTENTION.
OUT HERE WHEN I'M THIS CLOSE TO
A MILLION DOLLARS HIM RUNNING
HIS MOUTH COULD COST ME.
>> I WANT TO CLIMB UP.
YOU WANT TO GO UP?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> GET TWO GOOD FOOTHOLDS.
HERE'S THE HACKER.
>> SO CLOSE.
SO CLOSE.
>> ONE HACK AWAY.
>> COME ON, FINISH IT.
>> OH!
>> OW!
>> YOU OKAY, MAN?
>> HE'S GOING TO LOOK LIKE HIS
DAD.
>> MY SON IS BLOODYD FROM HERE
TO HERE, HIS CHEST, EVERYBODY'S
LIKE "ARE YOU OKAY?"
AND I'M LIKE "THAT'S MY BOY."
>> WE'VE GOT TO GET YOU INTO
SOME SALT WATER.
>> SHE HAS AN EXTRA SET OF EYES
AND EARS HERE.
IF THERE'S ANY KIND OF INTEL I
CAN GATHER.
>> THAT'S AWESOME, I LOVE THAT.
>> I'M TRYING TO THINK HOW I CAN
HELP YOU OUT.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
BECAUSE AT THIS POINT WE HAVE A
VERY STRONG FOUR ALLIANCE:
MALCOLM, DENICE, MICHAEL AND ME.
BUT I DON'T WANT MALCOLM IN THE
FINAL THREE BECAUSE HE WOULD
PROBABLY WIN IT.
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED LISA MADE
IT THIS FAR.
I LOOK UP TO HER FOR A REASON.
SHE ALWAYS SEEMS TO SAY THE
RIGHT THING.
SHE ALWAYS SEEMS TO DO THE RIGHT
THING.
SHE'S A REALLY GOOD GAME PLAYER.
SHE'S SUPERSMART, VERY BRIGHT,
SHE KNOWS HOW TO WIN.
>> I ORCHESTRATED THIS BLIND
SIDE OF MALCOLM RIGHT AFTER THE
MERGE.
HE DIDN'T SEE IT COMING.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO VOTE FOR
MICHAEL SKUPIN.
I FOUND MALCOLM'S HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL IN HIS BACK.
>> DID YOU TELL ANYBODY?
>> I TOLD MALCOLM THAT I FOUND
IT.
>> THAT WAS NICE OF YOU.
>> I'VE BEEN TOO NICE.
>> AND A MISTAKE.
>> AND A MISTAKE!
(LAUGHS)
I KNOW.
I'VE MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES OUT
HERE, JUSTICE.
IF I WERE TO START ALL OVER
AGAIN, WOULD I BETRAY PEOPLE,
HURT PEOPLE, NOT TELL THE TRUTH?
I DON'T KNOW.
BECAUSE IT'S EASY FOR ME TO SAY
IN MY HEAD IT'S JUST A GAME AND
REALLY PLAY THE GAME AND I COULD
HAVE PLAYED A GREAT GAME AND I
CAME OUT HERE STRONG.
>> Jeff: .
>> YOU WERE ALL ABOUT THE GAME
WHEN YOU LEFT.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
>> MY SISTER IS A VERY LOYAL
PERSON SO ANYTHING SHADY OR
UNDERHANDED WOULD BE SO
UNNATURAL FOR HER TO BEHAVE LIKE
THAT.
I HAVE TO BE HONEST.
LIKE, MALCOLM'S A THREAT, MAN.
>> MY JOB IS TO REMIND MY SISTER
TO THINK OF THIS AS A GAME:
OUTWIT, OUTLAST, OUTPLAY THE
OTHER CONTESTANTS.
>> YOU KNOW WORRYING THAT GOOD
BECAUSE OUR FOUR-PERSON ALLIANCE
IS VERY TIGHT.
EVEN THOUGH MALCOLM HAS AN IDOL.
HE CAN ONLY PLAY IT TOMORROW
NIGHT OR THE NEXT NIGHT.
>> SO HE'S -- DO YOU THINK HE'S
GOING TO PLAY IT?
>> WE'VE STUCK TO OUR WORD EVERY
TIME.
IT WOULD BE DUMB OF HIM TO PLAY
IT.
>> WHY DON'T YOU VOTE OUT
MALCOLM THEN?
>> WOULDN'T THAT BE CRAZY.
CARTER WOULD JOIN US WHERE WE
COULD HAVE A THREE-PERSON
ALLIANCE WITH LISA, I, AND
CARTER WE COULD TAKE MALCOLM OUT
AND AN IDOL AT ONE TIME AND
BLIND SIDE HIM.
WE COULD DO THAT.
>> THERE'S A PROBLEM WITH THAT:
I TRIED TO MAKE THAT BIG PLAY
AND AFTER THAT IT BLEW UP,
MESSED ME UP.
>> IT DIDN'T BLOW YOU UP.
IT GOT US HERE.
>> I DO KNOW IT'S A GAME AND I
LOVE THIS GAME.
BUT I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO STEP
OUTSIDE OF WHO I AM OUTSIDE THE
GAME TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> IF ABI, MICHAEL AND YOU AND
CARTER ALL VOTED MALCOLM, WOULD
THAT BE ENOUGH FOR HIM TO LEAVE?
>> YES.
>> OKAY, HELP EXPLAIN TO ME WHY
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO GET MALCOLM OUT
WOULD BE --
>> BECAUSE I GAVE MALCOLM MY
WORD.
>> SO THAT'S THE DECISION?
>> YES.
>> HOLDING ON TO YOUR WORD?
I KNEW THAT YOU HAD TO LIE TO
PLAY THIS GAME.
I KNEW IT WAS PART OF THE GAME
AND THAT EVERYBODY SIGNED UP
KNEW THAT YOU CAN'T TAKE PEOPLE
AT THEIR WORD.
>> EVEN WHEN YOU ACTUALLY
BETRAYED MALCOLM ALREADY HE WAS
LIKE "IT'S COOL.
IT'S A GAME" RIGHT?
SO HE MIGHT EVEN RESPECT THAT IN
THE END THAT YOU WERE ABLE TO DO
THAT.
>> WHEN SOMEBODY WHO KNOWS ME IS
ABLE TO REMIND ME OF THE CRYSTAL
CLEAR PICTURE THAT I'VE GOTTEN
ALL CONFUSED AND BEFUDDLED AND
FOGGY, IT WAS LIKE YEAH!
I CAN PLAY THIS GAME!
I CAN PLAY THIS GAME AND I CAN
PLAY IT WELL!
>> HEY, GUYS!
>> HOW'S THIS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT OUR
LOVELY EVENING?
OUR LIVING ROOM?
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
>> MY BROTHER HAS COME IN HERE
WITH SOME FRESH PERSPECTIVE AND
HE SAID, LISA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
YOU, MICHAEL, CARTER, ABI, BLIND
SIDE MALCOLM.
GET HIM OUT OF THERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MICHAEL?
>> I LOVE FRESH PERSPECTIVE AND
I LOVE FINAL THREE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL WIN BUT
I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO PLAY THE GAME BY THESE RULES
TO WIN.
HAVE THIS TIME WITH MY BROTHER.
BLESS ME, BLESS ABI AND CARTER
AS WE FINISH THESE DAYS, GIVE US
ALL STRENGTH.
LORD, WE DON'T PROPOSE TO GUESS
YOUR WILL AS MUCH ASK WE ASK
THAT YOU WOULD BLESS THIS PLAN
AND PROTECT IT AND IF YOU WANT
MALCOLM TO WIN OR CARTER OR
DENICE OR EVEN ABI, WE WANT
ULTIMATELY YOUR WILL TO BE DONE.
>> I DIDN'T THINK OF THAT.
THEY'RE GOING TO BOND OF JESUS.
>> THEY ARE GOING TO BOND OVER
JESUS.
>> I COULD HAVE GUESSED THAT IF
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
>> YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO
KICK ASS AT THE CHALLENGES.
IMMUNITY.
>> ONE OF THE BIGGEST FEARS I
HAVE AFTER HAVING THE LOVED ONES
HERE IS LISA.
SHE WAS AT ROCK BOTTOM
EMOTIONALLY AND WAS PLAYING WITH
HER HEART, AS SHE LIKES TO SAY.
AND I'M AFRAID THAT HER BROTHER,
WHO SEEMS LIKE A VERY
LEVEL-HEADED INTELLIGENT GUY
MIGHT HAVE SNAPPED HER BACK TO
HER SENSES AND GOT HER THINKING
ABOUT WHO SHE NEEDS TO BE
SITTING NEXT TO IN THAT FINAL
THREE TO HAVE A SHOT OF WINNING.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT JESUS
CHRIST WOULD LOOK LIKE PLAYING
"SURVIVOR."
>> SADLY, A LITTLE BIT LIKE
MALCOLM.
(LAUGHTER)
>> HE'D PROBABLY PLAY LIKE
CARTER, WHICH IS EVEN WORSE.
(LAUGHTER)
I DON'T THINK GOD CHOOSES SIDES.
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN PRAY FOR
YOUR FOOTBALL TEAM AND BECAUSE
YOU'RE PRAYING GOD IS GOING TO
CHOOSE THAT SIDE.
I THINK HE'S SO MUCH BIGGER THAN
THAT.
MALCOLM, NICE TO MEET YOU, MAN.
>> IT WAS A PLEASURE.
>> I HAD THOSE AND MAYBE THE
SHIRT OFF YOUR BACK, TOO?
>> YEAH.
>> SO IT WAS EASY TO PRAY AND
SAY WE HAVE A PLAN, WE WOULD
LOVE IT IF YOU BLESS IT BUT IF
YOU DON'T AND HAVE A BIGGER PLAN
WE'D TOTALLY TRUST THAT.
HE'S A WIN-WIN GOD.
MAYBE NOT EVERYBODY WINS THE
MILLION DOLLARS.
(LAUGHS)
BUT HE'S PRETTY RESOURCEFUL.
>> GIVE ME YOUR SHIRT.
(LAUGHTER)
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: YOU KNOW WHAT THAT
MEANS, ABI.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: GIVE IT BACK.
>> I FELL IN LOVE WITH IT.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP.
>.>> Jeff: WIN IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'LL
RACE ACROSS A BAMBOO BALANCE
BEAM TO A PLATFORM WHERE YOU
WILL FIND A HOOK ATTACHED TO
ROPE.
YOU'LL DROP IT IN WATER AND USE
THE HOOK TO RETRIEVE THREE BAGS.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THREE BAGS,
YOU'LL RACE TO THE FINISH AND
USE THE ROPE AND STICKS INSIDE
THE BAG TO FASHION A POLE.
ONCE THE POLE IS LONG ENOUGH YOU
WILL USE IT TO HIT A TARGET
DROPPING THE FLAG.
FIRST PERSON TO DROP THEIR FLAG
WINS IMMUNITY, IS GUARANTEED A
1-5 SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A 1-5 SHOT OF
WINNING THIS GAME, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN'S THERE!
LISA GETS TO THE SECOND
PLATFORM.
ABI'S THERE.
CARTER'S STILL STRUGGLING.
DENICE STILL STRUGGLING.
CARTER MAKES IT TO THE SECOND
PLATFORM.
EVERYBODY AT THAT PLATFORM
QUICKLY EXCEPT FOR DENICE, SHE'S
STRUGGLING.
MALCOLM HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
LISA HAS HER FIRST BAG.
ABI HAS A BAG.
DENICE IS NOW THERE.
CARTER HAS A BAG.
SKUPIN WITH HIS FIRST BAG.
DENICE HAS A BAG.
CARTER WITH HIS SECOND BAG.
THERE ARE THREE BAGS TOTAL.
LISA HAS HER SECOND BAG.
CARTER HAS THREE BAGS.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
MALCOLM WITH HIS SECOND BAG.
SKUPIN HAS HIS THIRD BAG, HE CAN
START HEADING BACK.
LISA HAS HER THIRD BAG.
IT'S CARTER, SKUPIN AND LISA
WITH ALL THREE BAGS.
MALCOLM HAS HIS THIRD BAG, HE'S
HEADED BACK.
DENICE HAS HER THIRD BAG, A BIG
COME FROM BEHIND FOR DENICE.
ABI HAS HER THIRD BAG.
EVERYBODY HEADING BACK.
LET'S GO, ABI, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
PICK IT UP!
ABI TAKING AS MUCH TIME AS SHE
CAN TO GET IN THE WATER.
AS IF THERE WAS NOTHING ATTACHED
TO THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU NEED TO ERECT A POLE LONG
ENOUGH AND STRONG ENOUGH TO
KNOCK OVER YOUR TARGET.
LISA'S ALREADY STARTED WORKING
ON HER POLE.
SKUPIN GETTING STARTED.
CARTER'S PUTTING SOME ROPE TO
STICKS.
MALCOLM STILL UNTYING.
ABI FINALLY JOINS THE GROUP.
THAT TOOK FOREVER!
LISA THE FIRST TO GIVE IT A
SHOT.
WILL IT DO IT.
VERY CLOSE.
IS IT STRONG ENOUGH?
NO, SHE'S SHORT, GOT TO GO BACK.
CARTER GIVING IT A SHOT.
SKUPIN GIVES IT A SHOT.
SKUPIN NOT LONG ENOUGH.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
IT WOULD BE SO NICE TO HAVE THAT
NECKLACE.
WILL IT BE CARTER?
NO!
HE'S VERY CLOSE.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
LISA, CARTER, SKUPIN NOW MAKING
ADJUSTMENTS, OPENING THE DOOR
FOR MALCOLM, ABI AND DENICE.
MALCOLM NOW GOING TO GIVE IT A
SHOT!
CARTER GIVING IT ANOTHER SHOT.
IT WOULD BE SO NICE TO HAVE
IMMUNITY AFTER 33 DAYS.
CARTER CLOSE.
CAN HE GET THERE?
HE'S RIGHT ON THE EDGE!
MALCOLM VERY CLOSE.
HE'S RIGHT ON THE TARGET.
SOMEBODY GOING TO BE VERY CLOSE
TO WINNING IMMUNITY RIGHT NOW.
MALCOLM VERY CLOSE.
AND HE KNOCKS IT OVER!
MALCOLM WINNING IMMUNITY, IS
SAFE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FIVE.
>> GOOD JOB, MALCOLM.
>> GOOD JOB, MALCOLM!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, COME ON
OVER.
FIRST WIN, STKPWHRAOEUG, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, FINALLY.
TOOK LONG ENOUGH.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM SAFE IN
TONIGHT'S COUNCIL, GUARANTEED A
SPOT IN THE FINAL FIVE AND ONE
STEP CLOSER TO HAVING A SHOT AT
THAT FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SADLY ONE OF THE FIVE OF YOU
WILL BE GOING HOME TONIGHT.
YOUR SHOT AT THE MONEY WILL BE
OVER.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO BUMMED!
I WAS SO READY TO PLAY THIS GAME
HARD AND MAKE A BIG MOVE AND
POOF.
AND MALCOLM WINS IMMUNITY!
AND LISA'S PLAN IS SHOT INTO
SMITHEREENS!
FEELING I'VE FELT THIS ENTIRE
GAME.
I FINALLY WON INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY AND I CAN ACTUALLY JUST
SIT AROUND CAMP AND NOT WORRY
ABOUT PEOPLE WANDERING OFF IN
PAIRS.
MY MIND GETS A BREAK.
JUST THE ICING ON THE CAKE.
WE'RE AT THE FINAL 6 NOW AND I
HAVE IMMUNITY.
I CAN'T BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT AND
THE LAST NIGHT I CAN PLAY THIS
IS AT THE FINAL 5.
I -- (LAUGHS)
I'M IN THE FINAL FOUR ON
"SURVIVOR" AND IT'S ONLY DAY 33.
TAKE TASTE IT.
OH, MY GOSH!
(LAUGHS)
>> WE DID PRAY THAT IF THIS WAS
NOT THE RIGHT WAY TO GO THAT GOD
WOULD CLOSE THE DOOR.
>> INTERESTING.
>> AND THAT DOOR WAS CLOSED.
AND EITHER THERE'S A BIGGER
PICTURE, BIGGER STORY, BIGGER
PLAN THAT WE CAN'T SEE.
>> LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THE ANT
ON THAT TREE.
>> OH, MY WORD, IT'S HUGE!
SO THIS APPARENTLY IS HIS WILL
FOR MALCOLM TO HAVE THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
I DON'T GET IT; I DON'T SEE IT.
>> OKAY, SO HE'S GOT SOMETHING
WAITING FOR US AT THE FINAL
FOUR.
SO AT THIS POINT WOULD YOU
RATHER VOTE ABI OR CARTER
TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO GET RID OF
CARTER.
I DON'T WANT TO GET RID OF HIM.
>> NOBODY WANTS TO GET RID OF
CARTER, I LOVE THE KID, TOO.
>> BUT IT'S THE GAME.
>> IT'S OBNOXIOUS.
DO WE GO WITH PEACE AROUND CAMP
OR STRATEGY?
CARTER ALMOST WON TODAY.
HE'S WON TWO, AT LEAST.
>> HE WAS THE FIRST ONE TO THE
STICKS.
>> HE REALLY IS.
HE'S -- ME AND YOU ARE PRETTY
EVEN, I THINK, PHYSICALLY.
WHAT UP?
>> WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
>> JUST CHATTING, DUDE.
>> AM I INTERRUPTING?
>> WELL, WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
YOU.
YOU CAN COME UP BUT WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
>> GOOD OR BAD.
>> WELL, WE HAVEN'T TALKED TO
THE GIRLS YET BUT IT CAN'T BE
MALCOLM TONIGHT.
(LAUGHS)
>> FINALLY.
>> SO, YEAH, WE'VE GOT TO MAKE A
DECISION.
IT JUST HASN'T BEEN MADE YET.
>> SO YOU KEEP ABI OVER ME?
>> WE'RE JUST TALKING ABOUT IT.
THE ONLY THING AGAINST YOU, THE
ONLY ONE THING AGAINST YOU IS
YOU'RE A THREAT AND EVERY OTHER
POSSIBLE THOUSAND REASONS ARE
AGAINST ABI.
>> SO OUT OF RESPECT FOR THIS
GAME AND OUT OF RESPECT FOR ME,
KEEP ME AROUND.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'LL LET YOU GUYS THINK BECAUSE
I RESPECT YOU GUYS.
>> IT'S TOTAL RESPECT.
>> I RESPECT YOUR GAME PLAY.
>> ON A PERSONAL LEVEL I KNOW
THIS GAME IS ABOUT STRATEGY AND
THIS GAME IS ABOUT WINNING
ULTIMATELY.
BUT EVERYONE AT OUR CAMP THIS
WHOLE TIME HAS BEEN TALKING
ABOUT KEEPING PEOPLE IN THIS
GAME WHO DESERVE TO BE IN THIS
GAME.
>> LOOK AT THESE FEET.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT SPREAD THING.
I HAVE WEBBED TOES RIGHT THERE.
>> DENICE, MALCOLM, SKUPIN AND
LISA ARE STAND-UP PEOPLE AND ABI
HAS BEEN REALLY MEAN TO PEOPLE
IN THIS GAME AND SO I MEAN TAKE
ME FURTHER IN THIS GAME THAN
SOMEONE WHO YOU GUYS DON'T
RESPECT AS A COMPETITOR.
>> CRAB-FLAVORED BEANS.
>> ACTUALLY, SITTING HERE, WHO
IS THE ONLY -- LISA, YOUR NAME
HAS NEVER BEEN WRITTEN DOWN.
>> SKUPIN HASN'T BEEN WRITTEN
DOWN.
>> AND SKUPIN HASN'T BEEN
WRITTEN DOWN.
>> I HAVEN'T, EITHER.
>> AND CARTER HASN'T.
>> AND I PUT UP THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND THE SIX OF YOU
WROTE MY NAME DOWN.
>> NO, WE SPLIT.
>> WHO DID YOU VOTE FOR, LISA,
THAT NIGHT?
>> I VOTED FOR YOU.
>> YOU VOTED FOR HE?
YOU WROTE MY NAME DOWN?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, WELL -- YOU SEEMED VERY
CLOSE TO ME, THOUGH, STILL.
MAYBE YOU'RE JUST TRYING TO GET
INFORMATION, BUT THAT'S FINE.
IT'S PART OF THE GAME.
>> AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME --
>> YOU'RE NOT CLOSER TO DENICE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF AT --
>> YOU ARE!
YOU ARE!
>> IF WE GET DOWN TO THE FINAL
FOUR, I MAY HAVE TO WRITE DOWN
DENICE'S NAME.
>> AND I WILL L NOT BEGRUDGE
YOU.
>> I'VE MADE A COMMITMENT TO HER
TO THE FINAL FOUR.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> I'M SAYING AFTER THE FINAL
FOUR --
>> YOU SAID MY WORD IS MORE
IMPORTANT TO ME THAN A MILLION
DOLLARS AND RIGHT NOW YOU'RE
TELLING ME A MILLION DOLLARS IS
MORE IMPORTANT TO ME THAN MY
WORD.
>> CAN I ASK A FAVOR?
IS THERE ANY WAY WE CAN LET THIS
CONVERSATION REST?
>> SURE.
>> IT'S EASY FOR YOU, DENICE,
YOU HERE IN THE FINAL FOUR
ALREADY!
>> NO, I'M NOT, ABI.
>> EASY FOR YOU, YOU'RE ALREADY
THERE!
>> ABI --
>> YOU ARE FOUR AGAINST TWO.
DON'T BE HYPOCRITICAL.
YOU'RE SITTING IN A VERY TIGHT,
SAFE SPOT.
CARTER AND I ARE NOT.
I WILL HAVE TO PLAY MY HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL NEXT TRIBAL.
SO IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> WELL --
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> AS MUCH AS I'M ENJOYING THIS.
>> I TRIED.
>> SINCE -- GOODNESS.
SINCE THE BEGINNING OF THIS GAME
EVERYONE HAS WANTED ABI GONE.
ABI IS SO DETRIMENTAL TO MORALE
AND JUST PEOPLE'S SMILES IN
GENERAL.
SHE'S LIKE A SOUL SUCKER AROUND
CAMP.
SHE'S LIKE THE DEMENTORS FROM
"HARRY POTTER."
>> SORRY SHE'S BEEN BULLYING
YOU.
>> I'M JUST OFFICIALLY OVER IT.
I HAVE TRIED TO BE KIND.
I HAVE TRIED TO BE
UNDERSTANDING.
YOU KNOW, AND IT'S LIKE -- RIGHT
THERE, GLARE ALL YOU WANT.
CUSS AT ME, DO WHATEVER YOU
WANT, IT HAS NO EFFECT AT THIS
POINT.
I DON'T CARE.
>> SHE'S EVERY PSYCHOLOGICAL
CONDITION ALL PACKED IN ONE.
>> VERY CHALLENGING TO DIAGNOSE,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> IT MAKES ME WONDER WHAT THE
HECK HER MOM IS LIKE.
(LAUGHS)
>> ABI'S PERSONALITY COMING OFF
STRONG, PART OF IT MAY BE
BECAUSE SHE'S FROM ANOTHER
COUNTRY.
I DON'T -- I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT IS NOT A CULTURAL THING.
IT'S HER PERSONALITY.
AND THERE WASN'T A SINGLE ONE OF
US SITTING THERE THAT DIDN'T GO
"AND NOW YOU'VE JUST GIVEN US
THE VERY REASON WE NEED TO VOTE
YOU OUT."
BECAUSE IT'S THIS HISTRIONIC
DRAMATIC PASSIVE AGGRESSIVE
MARTYR.
IT'S NOT CULTURE, IT'S THE
CULTURE OF ABI.
>> I AM DEFINITELY ON MY OWN OUT
HERE.
I'M TOTALLY FIGHTING FOR MYSELF.
I AM AN ALLIANCE OF ONE PERSON.
SO I JUST NEED TO PLAY SMART,
PLAY MY FANTASY IDOL, TRY AND
BLUFF IN THIS GAME.
THEY'RE NOT BELIEVING ME BUT,
HEY, IF YOU TELL A LIE LONG
ENOUGH EVERYONE STARTS TO
BELIEVE IT AND I'M CONVINCED IN
MY OWN LIE.
EVEN I AM BELIEVING MYSELF RIGHT
NOW.
(LAUGHS)
>> ABI CONTINUES TO THREATEN
THAT SHE HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
I THINK SHE'S OBNOXIOUS BUT EVEN
AS EMPTY AS WE THINK ABI'S
THREAT IS, IT REALLY IS
SOMETHING WE HAVE TO CONSIDER.
THAT BEING SAID, WE'RE REALLY
CONSIDERING GETTING RID OF THIS
ANGRY, UNSOCIALABLE BRAZILIAN
GIRL OVER A REALLY FIT ATHLETIC
GUY.
I'M CONSIDERING MAKING A REALLY
BAD STRATEGIC DECISION JUST FOR
MY, LIKE, MORALE.
THAT'S HOW TERRIBLE OF A HUMAN
BEING ABI IS, PLAIN AND SIMPLE,
CUT AND DRY.
IF ABI GOES HOME TONIGHT IT'S
BECAUSE SHE'S A BITCH.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
R.C., JEFF, ARTIS, KEITH AND
PENNER VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
MALCOLM, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA IF
YOU REALLY NEEDED IMMUNITY TODAY
OR WERE SAFE EITHER WAY?
>> YOU KNOW, I FELT SAFE.
I HAVE MY GROUP OF FOUR.
I TRUST THEM COMPLETELY.
I REALLY DID FEEL SAFE BUT THAT
DOESN'T MEAN I'M NOT EXCITED TO
HAVE IT FINALLY.
>> Jeff: REMIND ME WHO THE
GROUP OF FOUR IS.
>> MYSELF, DENICE, SKUPIN AND
LISA.
>> Jeff: SO, CARTER, IF THIS
GROUP OF FOUR IS TIGHT IT'S YOU
OR ABI GOING TONIGHT.
>> YEAH.
BUT I DON'T NECESSARILY
UNDERSTAND, ESPECIALLY WHEN
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF TALK ABOUT
TAKING THE PERSON THAT YOU FEEL
DESERVES IT OVER THE PERSON THAT
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU CAN BEAT.
SO I FEEL LIKE I'VE PLAYED A
GAME WORTHY ENOUGH TO BE TAKEN
TONIGHT TO THE FINAL FIVE AND
GIVEN A CHANCE TO FIGHT ANOTHER
DAY.
BECAUSE I DESERVE IT.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, CARTER'S
MAKING A PRETTY SIMPLE CASE,
SAYING LISTEN, PLAY THE GAME
WITH PEOPLE WHO DESERVE TO BE
THERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF CARTER'S MORE
OF A SON TO ME OR MORE OF A
FRIEND TO ME BUT WE CLICK VERY
WELL TOGETHER.
TO EVEN CONSIDER CARTER IT'S
ALMOST LIKE VOTING OFF MY OWN
KID.
TO EVEN CONSIDER IT.
>> Jeff: WHO YOU CALLED "THE
GREATEST HUMAN BEING" YOU KNOW.
>> ALMOST LIKE VOTING OFF MY OWN
KID, YES.
>> Jeff: LISA, IF YOU HAD TO
CHOOSE TONIGHT I'M GOING TO SIT
NEXT TO SOMEBODY THAT I THINK
DESERVES TO BE THERE OR I CAN
SIT NEXT TO SOMEBODY THAT I'M
PRETTY SURE I CAN BEAT, WHICH
WAY DO YOU SIT NOW AT THIS POINT
IN THE GAME?
>> I WOULD SIT NEXT TO SOMEBODY
I THINK I CAN BEAT.
YES, I WOULD LIKE TO BE NOBLER
THAN THAT, BUT WHY MAKE IT
HARDER THAN YOU HAVE TO?
>> Jeff: ABI, SURPRISED THAT
IT'S EVEN A CONSIDERATION THAT
YOU WON'T BE GOING HOME TONIGHT?
>> YEAH, I'M SURPRISED.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME I THINK I
HAVE A HUGE TOOL TONIGHT.
I FOUND THE FOURTH HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO I'M GOING TO PLAY IT AND I
DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: IS THIS NEW
INFORMATION OR SOMETHING THAT'S
BEEN TALKED ABOUT, DENICE?
>> NONE OF JUST SEEN IT, NONE OF
US HAVE SEEN ANY CLUES SO THE
ONLY THING WE CAN GO ON IS WHAT
ABI'S SHARING WITH US.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, DOES IT HELP
ABI'S GAME OR HURT IT BY NOT
SHOWINSHOWINSHOWING THIS IDOL?
>> WE'VE SEEN ABI PLAY FOR A
LONG TIME WITH AN IDOL AND I
THINK SHE'S SMART ENOUGH TO KNOW
IF SHE HAS IT SHE SHOULD BE
LEVERAGING IT MORE THAN SHE IS.
>> I'M JUST VERY PROTECTIVE OF
MYSELF AT THIS POINT AFTER
HEARING THAT I'M THE MOST
UNLIKABLE PERSON ON THE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: DENICE, HOW'S YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH ABI?
>> IT'S -- I THINK THE TENSION
IS STILL THERE.
BUT IT'S IMPROVED.
THAT'S ABOUT THE BEST THAT I CAN
SAY.
>> Jeff: SO HAS IT IMPROVED SO
MUCH THAT YOU ACTUALLY SEE HER
DIFFERENTLY AND MIGHT SAY, "YOU
KNOW WHAT?
YOU DESERVE TO GO TO THE END"?
>> MY -- PROBABLY NOT.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE CHANGING
MY ENTIRE STRATEGY THAT I HAD
COMING INTO THE GAME.
SO NO, I CAN'T SAY THAT THAT HAS
CHANGED.
>> Jeff: WHY DOES THAT MAKE
YOU LAUGH, ABI?
THAT'S NOT GOOD NEWS FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
>> IT'S HORRIBLE NEWS, BUT AT
THE SAME TIME I DON'T THINK I'M
BRINGING ANY TENSION.
SO I'M A LITTLE CONFUSED WITH
WHAT I JUST HEARD.
>> Jeff: MAYBE A BETTER WORD
IS "BAGGAGE."
>> I AM BAGGAGE?
>> Jeff: NO, NOT YOU.
BUT THE PAST 30 DAYS.
>> OH, YEAH, I UNDERSTAND, YEAH.
YEAH.
MAYBE THERE IS BAGGAGE.
I GUESS, YEAH.
>> Jeff: DENICE, DO YOU THINK
ABI CAN WIN THIS GAME IF SHE
GETS TO THE END?
>> I DON'T THINK SHE CAN WIN
THIS GAME.
IF SOMEBODY'S LOOKING IN THE
SPIRIT OF "SURVIVOR," THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR MORE OF A BALANCED
GAME BETWEEN THE SOCIAL, THE
STRATEGIC, THE PHYSICAL AND I
DON'T THINK THAT ABI'S BROUGHT
THOSE FULLY TO THE TABLE.
>> Jeff: WELL, THE SIX OF YOU
HAVE SURVIVED 33 DAYS IN THIS
GAME.
ONE OF YOU WILL NOT LIVE TO SEE
DAY 34.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CARTER, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, CARTER.
ABI.
: CARTER.
TWO VOTES CARTER.
CARTER.
THREE VOTES CARTER; ONE VOTE
ABI.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT, SIXTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
CARTER.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
CARTER, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE MADE IT
TO THE FINAL FIVE BUT THE
SMALLER THE NUMBERS GET THE MORE
DIFFICULT THE GAME BECOMES.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR" --
>> BE VERY CAREFUL.
DENICE, SHE KNOWS SHE CAN BEAT
YOU.
>> Jeff: INFORMATION FROM AN
UNLIKELY ALLY.
>> I THINK THIS ALLIANCE OF FOUR
YOU ARE TOTALLY ON THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: -- COULD FORCE LISA
TO MAKE HER BIGGEST MOVE YET.
>> IF WE KEEP ABI I HAVE
OPTIONS.
MAYBE TAKE TO THE END.
USE HER FOR MY BEST GAME PLAN.
>> THE REALIZATION THAT MY
"SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE IS OVER IS
WEIGHING HEAVILY ON ME.
IT DOES HURT TO KNOW THAT THAT
FOUR WOULD RATHER PLAY WITH
SOMEONE LIKE ABI WHO THEY FEEL
LIKE THEY CAN BEAT THESE NEXT
FEW DAYS AS OPPOSED TO ME.
I CAN UNDERSTAND IT, BUT IT
DOESN'T MEAN IT DOESN'T HURT.
THEY'RE PLAYING WITH THEIR HEADS