Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": 15 AMERICANS WERE
SHIPPED TO THE PHILIPPINES, AN
ISLAND NATION FULL OF DEADLY
ANIMALS AND FEROCIOUS STORMS.
AMONGST THE NEW SURVIVORS WERE
TWO FAMILIAR FACES--
MY NAME IS LISA WELCHEL.
I PLAYED THE CHARACTER BLAIR
WARNER ON "THE FACTS OF LIFE."
I'M JEFF KENT.
I PLAYED 17 YEARS IN MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL.
THIS WILL BE REAL FUN FOR ME.
Jeff: THE NEW CASTAWAYS
WERE JOINED BY THREE PAST
SURVIVORS, ALL RETURNING FROM
DEVASTATING EVACUATIONS.
ALL THREE HAVE ONE THING NONE OF
THE REST OF YOU HAVE--
EXPERIENCE.
THIS SEASON, THE CASTAWAYS WERE
DIVIDED INTO THREE TRIBES, EACH
JOINED BY ONE RETURN PLAYER.
JONATHAN PENNER JOINED KALABAW.
MICHAEL SKUPIN TO TANDANG.
AND RUSSELL SWAN TO MASTING.
EITHER THESE PEOPLE WILL RUN
WITH ME OR I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
RUN THEM OVER.
Jeff: YOUR TIME STARTS NOW.
CUT IT!
IS YOUR LEG OKAY, BUDDY?
WITHIN THE FIRST THREE
MINUTES I POSSIBLY COULD HAVE
TORN MY M.C.L., AND IF MY
TEAMMATES SMELL BLOOD THEY'LL
KICK ME OFF THIS ISLAND REAL
FAST.
Jeff: IT WAS CLEAR
EXPERIENCE WAS KEY WHENEROUS
EXPEL PENNER FOUND CLUES TO THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS.
FOUND THE CLUE!
Jeff: BUT FOR PENNER IT
WASN'T ALL LUCK.
I AGREE.
I THINK HE HAD HIS TIME AND
HE'S OUT AS SOON AS WE CAN GET
HIM OUT.
Jeff: AT TANDANG,
ABPIERKS AND R.C. WERE ALL
SMILES.
THEY JOINED A MAJORITY ALLIANCE
OF FOUR, MAKING LISA, THE FORMER
TEEN STAR, AN EARLY TARGET.
I DO NOT TRUST HER.
DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE LISA.
LISA IS WAY FAMOUS.
I DON'T KNOW HER STRATEGY FOR
NOT REVEALING WHO SHE IS.
Jeff: AT THE FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
I WANT YOU TWO TO DO THE
PUZZLE.
Jeff: RUSSELL'S BOSSINESS
BACKFIRED.
KEEP GOING!
DON'T LOOK!
Jeff: KALABAW FIRST TO
FINISH.
TANDANG SURVIVES IMMUNITY AS
WELL.
I TOLD YOU I'M NOT GOOD AT
PUZZLE.
BACK AT CAMP, ALL EYES ORP
RUSSELL.
HONESTLY, I CAN'T STAND
HE'S GOING HOME.
Jeff: UNTIL ZANE SHIFTED
THE BLAME TO HIMSELF.
THREE DAYS IN, BROTHER, I
AIN'T BUILT FOR IT.
NOTHING AGAINST ZANE, BUT
THIS IS NOT THE POINT IN THE
GAME WHERE YOU CAN HAVE WEAK
PLAYERS.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THEY CALLED OUT RUSSELL.
HE TOLD ME, IF WE LOSE, IT'S
YOUR FAULT.
Jeff: IN THEIND.
I HAVE SO MUCH MORE TO GIVE.
AND HOPE I GET THAT
OPPORTUNITY G.
Jeff: RUSSELL BARELY
ESCAPED.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
17 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
WHY?
WE WENT TO TRIBAL TONIGHT.
I KNEW MY HEAD WAS POTENTIALLY
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
I GOT INTO THIS KIND OF TRIBAL
CHIEF THING WHERE IT WAS MY WAY
OR THE HIGHWAY.
AND IT ALMOST GOT ME VOTED OUT.
LET'S JUST NOT DO THAT AGAIN.
HOW ABOUT THAT.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
SO, MY STRATEGY GOING FORWARD
IS TO STEP BACK AND LET THEM
RISE AND FALL ON THE DECISIONS
THAT THEY MAKE.
THAT WAY, IF WE CRASH AND BURN,
THEN THEY CAN BE ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK AS OPPOSED TO ME.
COME OVER HERE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
RIGHT HERE.
IT IS SO FREAKING COLD.
IF I DID NOT CUDDLE I WOULD HAVE
FROZE TO DEATH.
THERE'S NOTHING GOING ON BETWEEN
US.
YOU KNOW, WHEN IT'S COLD, YOU
NEED TO CUDDLE UP TO SOMEONE.
WHEN I FIRST SAW ANGIE, I
KEPT HAVING TO REMIND MYSELF,
DON'T GET BOOTY BLINDED.
DOARNT GET BOOTY BLINDED.
YOU'RE HERE TO PLAY "SURVIVOR"
TO MAKE A MILLION DOLLARS AND GO
HOME.
THERE'S NO DENYING, THAT'S A
GOOD-LOOKING GIRL.
SHHH!
SO I WAKE UP IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE NIGHT, AND MALCOLM AND ANGIE
THEY'RE, LIKE, CUDDLING, FULL ON
CUDDLING.
IT'S THE SAME TRAP THAT IS SET
EVERY TIME, AND ANGIE LITERALLY,
IT'S A BOOBY TRAP, AND MALCOLM
IS FALLING FOR IT.
I WAS NOT BORN YESTERDAY.
OKAY.
AS A TRIBE, WE NEED TO BE AWARE
THAT THAT IS GOING ON BECAUSE
THOSE TWO ARE DANGEROUS
TOGETHER.
ONE HAS GOT TO GO, PERIOD.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
THE WEATHER IS HORRIBLE.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY HORRIFIC.
EVERYTHING IS SOAKING WET.
AND I WAS, LIKE, NERVOUS ABOUT
THE RICE GETTING MOLDY.
SO I STUCK MY HAND IN JUST TO
MAKE SURE, AND I TOOK THE BAG
BEFORE TO FIND EYE CLUE AND I
DIDN'T FIND ANYTHING, AND WHICH
TIME I FOUND IT RIGHT AWAY.
IT'S GOOD.
DO YOU WANT TO JUSTRAPHY IT
HERE FOR NOW?
LISA WAS LOOKING OVER MY
SHOULDER SO I WAS HOPING SHE
DIDN'T REALLY SEE MY FACE OR
GIVE AWAY ANYTHING.
SOMETIMES I FEEL ABI COULD
POTENTIALLY USE ME IN THE
FUTURE, BUT I FEEL LIKE I CAN
USE HER IN THE FUTURE SO IF I
GET HER ON MY SIDE, SOLIDIFY HER
WITH ME THAT WILL BE THE
STRONGEST TWO-SOME AT LEAST IN
OUR PRIDE.
I KNEW IT.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU.
IT'S AT CAMP.
THIS STAYS BETWEEN US?
OF COURSE.
I MEAN, I TRUST PETER AND I
TRUST MICHAEL BUT, LIKE, THIS IS
FOR US, FOR THE FUTURE.
YEAH, LET'S GET WATER AND
HIDE THIS.
ME AND ABI REALLY CLICKED SINCE
DAY ONE BUT SINCE HE HAVEN'T
BEEN TO GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL OUR
ALLIANCE HASN'T BEEN TEST YET.
I SHARED THE CLUE WITH HER AND
THAT SHOULD BE PROOF ENOUGH THEY
TRUST HER.
HOPEFULLY NONE OF THEM FOUND
IT, FIRST.
UNDER OUR NOSES.
IT IS GREAT THAT R.C. WANTS
TO SHARE THE IDOL WITH ME.
I WAS VERY LUCKY TO CATCH HER
FINDING THE CLUE, SO SHE HAS NO
OTHER CHOICE.
BUT A SIDE OF ME TELLS ME TO BE
CAREFUL.
NO.
YEAH, THAT'S NEW.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF I CAN
TRUST R.C. ALL THE WAY, BECAUSE
I FEEL THAT SHE'S GETTING A
LITTLE BIT TOO CLOSE TO MIKE.
WHAT WERE YOU GUYS TALKING
ABOUT?
IF YOU WANT TO GET YOUR
CLOTHES OUT OF RAIN.
I CATCH THEM WHISPERING A
LITTLE TOO MUCH, I CATCH THEM
SWITCHING CONVERSATIONS WHEN I
WALK IN.
IF SHE SCREWS ME OVER, THAT'S
IT.
SHE'S DEAD TO ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS, MIKE IS
LIKE MY FATHER.
I LIKE MIKE, BUT THE PLAN IS
STILL IN EFFECT.
THIS IS A GAME.
YOU.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU LIKE
MIKE OR NOT.
YOU'RE PLAYING A GAME.
YOU AND HIM GO OFF TOGETHER AND
YOU'RE ALWAYS WHISPERING.
YEAH, BUT I FEEL THE SAME WAY
ABOUT YOU AND PETE.
BUT WE DON'T SWITCH
CONVERSATIONS WHEN PEOPLE WALK
UP TO US.
YOU AND MIKE DO, AND IT'S
OBVIOUS.
I DON'T THINK WE DO.
I THOUGHT ABI WAS MY NUMBER TWO.
I THOUGHT SHE COULD HANDLE IT
BUT SHE CAN GO OFF LIKE THAT AND
THAT REALLY MAKES ME NERVOUS.
SHE THINKS I COULD BE MAKING
SUBALLIANCES AND I'M NOT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PROVE THAT
TO HER.
I WOULDN'T LIE TO YOU.
I HAVEN'T LIED TO YOU, AND YOU
HAVE NO REASON TO THINK THAT I
WOULD LIE TO YOU.
I AM YOUR FRIEND.
ME, TOO.
BUT IF YOU ( BLEEP ) WITH ME
YOU'RE DEAD.
SERIOUSLY, ARE YOU DONE.
JUST LETTING YOU KNOW.
I'M STRUGGLING A LITTLE BIT
WITH THIS WEATHER, BUT I PLAYED
BASEBALL FOR 17 YEARS AND, YOU
KNOW, "SURVIVOR" IS GOING TO BE
A LONG SEASON FOR ME.
I'M UP TO THE CHALLENGE.
I KNOW HOW TO WAIT PEOPLE OUT.
BASEBALL WE PLAYED FOR SIX
MONTHS.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING LEFT
IN THE TANK OCTOBER, THEN YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO BE A CHAMPION.
MAYBE WE SHOULD PLAY INSIDE
GAMES LIKE ON A RAINY DAY AT
HOME.
WE COULD DRAW SOME SQUARES IN
THE GROUND.
AND ROCKS.
AND A CHECKERBOARD.
YOU GUYS WANT TO DO THAT?
THE WAY THINGS ARE GOING WITH
MY KNEE SITTING AROUND WATCHING
THE RAIN FALL COULD BE GOOD FOR
ME RIGHT NOW.
I'M MAKING SURE I TAKE CARE OF
MY KNEE AND HAVE ENOUGH ENERGY
SO OUR TEAM CAN WIN.
HOW MANY SQUARES ACROSS?
17.
WHAT ARE YOU DRAWING?
WE'RE MAKING A CHECKERBOARD.
AWESOME.
BETTER HURRY UP BEFORE THE
RAIN WASHES THE GAME AWAY.
THE DOWNSIDE IN THE CONSTANT
RAIN, THE IDOL IS SOMEWHERE
RIGHT IN OUR CAMP AND I CAN'T
GET THEM OUT OF THE SHELTER.
I NEED 10 MINUTES JUST SO I CAN
DIG AROUND AND GET THIS DAMN
IDOL.
IT'S THERE, IT'S WAITING FOR ME.
I CAN'T GET TO IT!
JONATHAN, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THIS?
THIS RAIN?
NO, NO, I'M OKAY.
THE CAVE?
I CAN GRAB A LITTLE TINDER AND
GO THERE.
I'M GO WITH YOU.
I'M ACTUALLY GOING TO GO FOR
A DIP.
I'M SOAKED ANYWAY, I DON'T CARE.
WE'RE GOING TO THE CAVE.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A FIRE.
BE CAREFUL!
HAVE FUN!
YOU, TOO, SWEETHEART.
BYE.
LUCKILY, THEY'RE SO CONCERNED
ABOUT THE RAIN, THEY'VE ALL GONE
TO A CAVE.
THE CAMP IS EMPTY.
THE CLUE SAID IT WAS RIGHT UNDER
MY NOSE.
IT'S RIGHT UNDER MY NOSE.
WASTE, OUR TIME, GUYS, UNLESS
YOU GOT ANYTHING UP THERE,
CARTER.
WHERE THE HELL IS THE DAMN
IDOL?
COME ON, MAN.
WELL, FLINT WILL WORK
REGARDLESS HOW WET IT IS.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
I NEVER HAD THE IMMUNITY
IDOL.
I'VE NEVER HAD INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY AT ALL.
THIS IS A KEY TO THE GAME.
I'VE GOT TO FIND THIS THING
BEFORE THEY GET BACK TO CAMP.
AND I'M SAYING JUST STAY CALM.
WHO KNOWS HOW LONG YOU HAVE
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
MY LENS WASHED OUT.
I WAS LOOKING FOR MY GLASSES, I
COULDN'T FIND THEM.
YOU FOUND THEM?
YEAH, IT WAS SO WET I LOOKED
UP AND MY LENS WASHED RIGHT OUT.
DAWSON COMES INTO THE CAMP SO I
MADE UP THIS INSANE STORY I LOST
MY GLASSES AND HAD TO GO UNDER
TO GET THEM BECAUSE THE RAIN
WASHED MY CONTACT LENS OUT,
WHICH WAS RIDICULOUS.
A LIE.
I CAN'T FIND IT ANYWHERE.
IT'S RIGHT UNDER MY NOSE.
IT'S GOT TO BE THERE, IN THE
CAMP, UNDER MY NOSE.
I'M GETTING MORE AND MORE
FRUSTRATED, AND THEN A LIGHT
BULB GOES OFF.
IF I HAD OPENED THE CLUE WHERE
THE CLUE WAS, ON TOP OF THE
RICE, THERE'S A LITTLE WOODEN
BULL WITH A VERY PROMINENT NOSE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THREE
TRIES, I HAVE THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT'S FANTASTIC.
THE IDOL IS RIGHT UNDER YOUR
NOSE.
YOU HAVE THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU FEEL THAT YOU CAN
DANCE FOREVER, NOT CAN TOUCH
YOU.
OF COURSE, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I KNOW A LOT OF GUYS WHO THOUGHT
I'M GOING TO DANCE ALL THE WAY
TO THE MILLION AND THEY GOT
BLINDSIDED.
THOSE ARE MISTAKES -- WELL,
LISTEN-- THAT'S A MISTAKE THAT
I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE, I HOPE.
YEAH!
I'M ON FIRE!
GOOD MORNING, EVERYBODY.
GOOD MORNING.
SO I WAKE UP ON DAY FIVE, AND
MALCOLM AND ANGIE ARE CUDDLING
AGAIN.
AND I'M, LIKE, I WANT ONE OF YOU
OUT.
MALCOLM IS CLEARLY MORE USEFUL.
SO IN ORDER TO GET ANGIE OUT, I
KNEW I HAD TO GET RUSSELL ON MY
SIDE.
NOW THE CUDDLING HAPPENING
THEY'RE GETTING CLOSER.
THEY DEFINITELY LOOK LIKE
SOMETHING IS GOING ON.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
( LAUGHTER )
WHERE PEOPLE SLEEP IN THE
SHELTER IS PRETTY TELLING.
AND ANGIE, HOT YOUNG CHICK
WITH-- I MEAN, IT LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S GOT SOME BOOB THING GOING
ON.
THEY'RE POPPING UP ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
AND I DON'T BLAME MALCOLM FOR
WANTING TO SLAP AND TICKLE, BUT
I CAN'T GET DOWN WITH THAT.
YOU GET YOUR BANG ON SOMEWHERE
ELSE, BECAUSE "SURVIVOR"
COUPLES, YOU WANT TO WHACK THAT
THING DOWN REAL QUICK.
I WOULD HAVE!
NO, YOU WOULDN'T HAVE.
YES, I WOULD HAVE.
ANGE AND MALCOLM ARE A PAIR
AND WHAT'S SCARIER THAN AN
ALLIED PAIR.
WHO ARE JUST NATURALLY, I LIKE
YOU, NO MATTER WHAT.
THERE'S DEFINITELY SOME OF
THAT.
I'M HEARING, LIKE, MOANS AND CUD
KENNEDY LING AND ALL THAT STUFF.
I'M SORRY.
THIS IS WHAT I'M THINKING.
IF WE DON'T WIN IMMUNITY, SHE'S
GOT TO GO HOME.
THEY SAY MALCOLM AND ANGIE AS
THIS BIG COUPLE, SOME THREAT,
HEY, WE NEED TO SPLIT THAT UP.
BUT MALCOLM AND I ARE IN AN
ALLIANCE.
I THINK PART OF IT IS A
24-YEAR-OLD GUY SNUGGLING UP TO
SOMETHING THAT IS REALLY NICE TO
SNUGGLE UP TO BUT NOW THERE ARE
THESE HUGE TARGETS ON THEIR
BACK.
THIS MORNING, THERE WAS A
VERY STRANGE VIBE GOING AROUND
CAMP.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT WAS GOING ON,
BUT NOW I'M NERVOUS THE REST OF
THE TRIBE IS FREAKING OUT ABOUT
ME AND ANGIE COUPLING UP.
THEY COULD SEE THAT AS A THREAT
POTENTIALLY, AND IF THAT'S THE
CASE, WE COULD BE IN TROUBLE.
I JUST SIT HERE AND WAIT AND
WAIT.
WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE FOOD?
HAM AND CHEESE SANDWICH.
I LOVE FRENCH FRIES.
I CAN EAT FRENCH FRIES ALL DAY
LONG.
I'M AN INTROVERT BY NATURE,
SO I DON'T DO WELL WITH
CHIT-CHAT.
I'M JUST NOT VERY GOOD AT THAT.
I'M VERY, VERY SHY, SO IF I'M ON
THE STAGE, I CAN BE BEHIND A
ROLE.
BUT IN REAL LIFE, MY TENDENCY IS
JUST TO WITHDRAW AND NOT LET
ANYBODY IN.
SHE'S GONE.
SHE JUST DISAPPEARS WAY TOO
MUCH.
SHE'S OFF LOOKING FOR THE
IMMUNITY IDOL.
I FEEL LIKE SINCE WE'RE SO
GOOD ON OUR FIVE THEN, YOU KNOW,
WE JUST HAVE TO WATCH HER.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE TO WATCH OUT
FOR, NOT THE IDOL.
THAT'S WHY SHE'S LOOKING FOR
THE IDOL RIGHT NOW BECAUSE SHE
KNOWS.
I THINK THAT LISA IS A LITTLE
BIT SNEAKY.
SHE'S JUST, LIKE, AN OUTSIDER.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE SHE'S TRYING
HARD ENOUGH TO CONNECT WITH THE
TRIBE.
WE CREATED AN ALLIANCE, AND SHE
WASN'T A PART OF IT.
BECAUSE SHE WASN'T CONNECTING
WITH ANYBODY ELSE.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE I'M FITTING
IN.
I'M ALREADY ON THE OUTSIDE AND
DON'T REALLY HAVE SOMEBODY THAT
I CAN TRUST OR TALK TO.
I'VE BEEN ON MY OWN SINCE I WAS
12.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I MOVED TO
CALIFORNIA TO BE ON THE "MICKEY
MOUSE CLUB" AND I LEFT MY
FAMILY.
SO I'M VERY USED TO JUST TAKING
CARE OF MYSELF.
SO I THINK IN REAL LIFE I'M
TRYING TO LEARN TO OPEN UP AND
TRUST MORE AND DEPEND ON OTHER
PEOPLE, BUT THIS IS NOT THE
PLACE TO EXPERIMENT WITH THAT.
OBVIOUSLY, SHE DOESN'T HAVE
IT.
RIGHT, BECAUSE SHE'S STILL
LOOKING.
SHE'S LIKE A GOG DOGTHAT
KEEPS ESCAPING THE FENCE IN THE
BACKYARD.
EVENTUALLY YOU JUST HAVE TO
SHOOT IT.
I THINK WE'RE ALL IN
AGREEMENT, RIGHT?
OKAY, SHE'S COMING BACK.
IT'S HARD BEING ON THE
OUTSIDE, AND, YOU KNOW, I JUST--
MAYBE I'M NOT JUST NOT ABLE TO
PLAY THIS GAME.
DOWN, THIS IS THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING RIGHT NOW.
NO FIRE, THAT'S-- THAT'S DEADLY.
THE LAST TIME I PLAYED THIS
GAME, I WENT OUT, THE PLACE WAS
RAINING.
I COME BACK IN, IT'S RAINING
AGAIN.
SO I GUESS WE'RE JUST GOING TO
BE WET AND MISERABLE AND IT'S
JUST GOING TO SUCK THE B.S..
ARE YOU NOT COLD?
THAT'S WHY I KEEP RUNNING
AROUND, TO KEEP FROM GETTING
COLD.
I HAVEN'T BEEN THIS WET IN MY
LIFE.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
IT HASN'T STOPPED RAINING FOR
MORE THAN HALF AN HOUR SINCE WE
GOT HERE.
RUSSELL'S ON FIRE DUTY AND ME
AND DENISE ARE JUST TRYING TO
KEEP THE SHELTER IN ONE PIECE,
AND ROXY IS JUST OUT OF IT IT.
SHE'S NOT WORKING.
HER MIND'S NOT IN IT.
AND EVERYONE'S NOTICING IT.
THIS IS CRAZY.
IT'S JUST WATER.
WE'RE ALL GOOD.
BEING IN SEMINARY SCHOOL AND
BEING SOMEONE OF CHRISTIAN
FAITH, I THOUGHT THAT WOULD GIVE
ME GREAT STRENGTH WITHIN THIS
GAME.
BUT WITH IT BEING SO RAINY AND
SO FREEZING COLD, I JUST CAME TO
THE REALIZATION THAT I'M NOT IN
MY COMFORT ZONE AT ALL.
TALK TO ME GIRL.
WHAT'S GOING ON OVER THERE?
DON'T HOLD IT IN.
THERE'S A LOT TO IT.
BUT TRUST ME, WE LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE AN IMPORTANT PART OF THIS
FAMILY.
AND WE NEED YOU.
I HAVEN'T HAD A GOOD NIGHT'S
SLEEP SINCE I'VE GOTTEN HERE,
AND TO BE IN A PLACE WHERE YOU
LITERALLY HAVE NOTHING, NONE OF
YOUR FRIENDS.
YOU HAVE NONE OF YOUR FAMILY.
YOU DON'T HAVE YOUR CHURCH.
LIKE, RIGHT NOW, I'M
ENCOUNTERING ALL OVER AGAIN, AND
IT'S NOT EASY.
OH, LOOK IT, THE SUN.
YA!
YOU CAN BELIEVE IT?
FINALLY.
THANK YOU, GOD.
YOU HEAR EVERY PRAYER, GOD.
YOU ARE LOVING.
YOU ARE JUST.
GLORY BE TO YOUR NAME, GOD.
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT IF SHE'S
SPEAKING IN TONGUES OR SAYING A
PRAYER.
I'M SURPRISED.
I THOUGHT SHE WOULD HAVE A
LITTLE BIT MORE STRENGTH OF
CHARACTER THAN THIS.
IT MAKES ME REALLY NERVOUS,
RUSSELL.
I KNOW.
ROXY'S, SHE'S PRAYING FOR
SUNSHINE FROM GOD.
IF IT WORKS FOR HER, FANTASTIC.
I'M RESPECTFUL, BUT IT'S JUST
NOT MY GIG.
I DON'T PRAY FOR ANYTHING
ANYTHING THAT'S GOING TO GET ME
TO THE END OF THE GAME, IT'S
GOING TO BE ME.
REPORTER, LET'S GET READY TO
KICK SOME BUTT, PERIOD, END OF
DISCUSSION.
WE HAVE ANOTHER CHALLENGE
COMING UP, AND NOT ONCE DOES MY
MIND GO TO, GOD, HELP ME WIN
THIS CHALLENGE.
NO, DIG IN.
DIG DEEP.
AND MAKE IT HAPPEN.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
KALABAW AND TANDANG GET, YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW MATSING
TRIBE.
ZANE VOTED OUT AT THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
I'LL TAKE BACK THE IDOLS.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, TWO
MEMBERS FROM EACH TRIBE WILL
PULL A SLED OUT TO RETRIEVE
BUNDLES OF PUZZLE PIECES.
THEY COME BACK TO THE START, THE
NEXT PAIR GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL THE
PIECES, ONE PERSON WILL SERVE AS
YOUR CALLER AND THEY WILL TRY TO
HELP TWO OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS
SOLVE A GIANT PUZZLE.
THE FIRST TWO TRIBES TO GET IT
RIGHT WIN IMMUNITY AND ARE SAFE
FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
YEAH!
Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH.
OH!
Jeff: BLANKETS, PILLOWS,
AND A TARP.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH.
TARP!
Jeff: AND A TARP FOR THE
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH.
HUGE STAKES.
WITH THREE SMALL TRIBES YOU DO
NOT WANT TO FALL BEHIND IN
NUMBERS.
TANDANG AND KALABAW YOU'RE EACH
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
TANDANG WHO IS SITTING THIS ONE
OUT.
I'LL SIT OUT.
ABI TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
I'LL SIT OUT, JEFF.
>
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO RUN TWICE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO TWICE?
NOT REALLY.
OKAY, COULD YOU GO TWICE?
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN DRINKING
LESS WATER SO IT DOESN'T MAKE
SENSE FOR ME TO GO TWICE.
I'M JUST LETTING YOU GUYS KNOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
Jeff: CARTER FOR KALABAW,
AND PETE AND SKUPIN FOR TANDANG,
AND RUSSELL AND ANGIE FROM
MATSING.
ONLY FIVE PEOPLE LEFT.
MATSING DOES NOT WANT TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AGAIN.
SKUPE AND I KNOW PETE DOING NICE
WORK WITH THE SLED.
SKUPIN AND PETE GOT THEIR PIECES
AND ARE HEADING BACK.
JEFF AND CARTER HEADING BACK.
RUSSELL AND ANGIE, THEY'RE HUNG
UP.
NOW THE PIECES ARE STARTING TO
FALL OFF.
TANDANG OFF TO A FAST START.
KALABAW RIGHT BEHIND.
MATSING, ONCE AGAIN IN LAST
PLACE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN GO.
COME ON, KEEP GOING!
Jeff: KATY AND PENNER FOR
KALABAW.
RUSSELL AND ANGIE HAVE TO GET
THEIR PIECES BACK.
THEY'RE ALREADY TIRED.
MALCOLM AND ROXY NOW HEADING OUT
FOR MATSING.
MATSING WAY BEHIND EARLY IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
KALABAW GOING TO TAKE THEM OVER,
PASS THEM BY.
MALCOLM AND ROXY PICKING UP IN
TIME.
THEY'VE GOT THEIR SECOND SET.
MALCOLM IS PULLING IT ALONE.
ARTIS AND R.C. SLOWING DOWN.
THEY'VE NOW BEEN CAUGHT BY
MALCOLM.
MATSING'S MADE UP A LOT OF TIME.
CARTER AND JEFF HEADING OUT FOR
THE THIRD AND FINAL SET OF
PIECES FOR KALABAW.
PETE AND SKUPIN HEADING BACK OUT
FOR TANDANG.
RUSSELL AND ANGIE ARE GOING TO
GO BACK OUT AND RUSSELL IS
ALREADY TRIPPING OVER THE ROPES
THE SECOND TIME OUT.
JEFF AND CARTER NOW HEADING BACK
WITH THAT THIRD SET OF PUZZLE
PIECES.
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
FASTER!
Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE IS
EXHAUSTING.
SKUPEIP AND PETE EXHAUSTED.
RUSSELL, STEP BY STEP PULLING
THAT SLED.
ANGIE STRUGGLING.
KALABAW'S FIRST BACK.
UNLOAD THE PIECES.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
R.C. AND PETE WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE FOR TANDANG.
MALCOLM AND RUSSELL WITH A LOT
OF TIME TO MAKE UP.
THEY LOST THE FIRST CHALLENGE,
DO NOT WANT TO LOSE AGAIN.
ANGIE ON THE GROUND OUT OF IT.
R.C., YOU NEED A THREE RIGHT
IN A ROW.
RIGHT AFTER THAT.
Jeff: THE COMMUNICATION
BETWEEN THE CALLERS AND THE
PUZZLE SOLVERS WILL BE THE
DIFFERENCE IN THIS CHALLENGE.
NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
PUT A CORNER PIECE ON THIS
SIDE.
HEY!
THERE GU.
RIGHT THERE!
PUT YOUR LONG PIECE--
THAT'S IT, THAT'S IT.
PUT IT DOWN.
Jeff: KALABAW HAS THEIR
FIRST PUZZLE COMPLETED.
TANDANG HAS THEIR FIRST PUZZLE
COMPLETED VERY QUICKLY.
RUSSELL, TAKE A THREE.
ALL RIGHT, GO TO SECOND.
GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
Jeff: RUSSELL AND MALCOLM
SOLVED THEIR FIRST PUZZLE.
WE'VE GOT A CHALLENGE NOW.
THAT IS ONE ON THE RIGHT
SIDE!
NO 2s?
TURN THAT AROUND.
TURN THAT BACK AROUND, JEFF.
Jeff: NOBODY LISTENING TO
DANA.
THERE'S A YELLOW ONE RIGHT IN
FRONT OF YOU, PETE.
GOT IT.
WHOO!
YES!
Jeff: TANDANG HAS THEIR
SECOND PUZZLE FINISHED.
THEY'RE NOW WORKING ON THEIR
THIRD AND FINAL PUZZLE.
ONE MORE.
LIKE TETRIS.
Jeff: MATSING WAS OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE AND THEY'RE NOW
BACK IN IT.
THEY'RE WORKING ON THEIR THIRD
PUZZLE.
SUDDENLY JEFF AND PENNER ARE NOW
BEHIND.
ANOTHER DANA, WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT?
THAT PIECE IS NOT GOING TO
WORK.
COME OLISTEN UP.
STLIED SLIDEYOUR 3 ALL THE WAY
TO THE RIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
Jeff: EVERYBODY WORKING ON
THE THIRD PUZZLE.
THAT WON'T GO, R.C.
YOU'VE GOT A COUPLE OF LONG
PIECES?
PUT A 3 PIECE IN THE MIDDLE.
THERE YOU GO!
DO YOU HAVE ANOTHER L?
PUT IT RIGHT HERE IN THE FAR
LEFT CORNER.
PETE, PETE.
BUT THAT IN THE CORNER!
PUT IT IN THE CORNER.
THAT'S IT!
Jeff: TANDANG FINISHES
FIRST AND WINS IMMUNITY PLUS
TARP AND BLANKETS.
YES, WHOO!
YES!
Jeff: WE ARE STILL FIGHTING
FOR SECOND PLACE.
KEEP DIGGING!
PENNER!
PENNER, RIGHT HERE!
THERE IS NO 3.
THERE IS A 3 RIGHT HERE.
ONE BIG L.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, HERE WE GO.
NOT LIKE THAT.
L, RIGHT THERE!
PUT IT IN, RIGHT THERE, GET
IT!
KEEP GOING!
PUT IT IN!
RIGHT THERE!
GET IT!
Jeff: KALABAW WINS IMMUNITY
AND TARP.
YOU GOT IT!
MATSING GOES TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
FOR THE SECOND STRAIGHT TIME.
TANDANG, CONGRATULATIONS.
COME GET YOUR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
YOU NOW HAVE TARP AND COMFORT.
OH, WOW.
Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
KALABAW, COME ON OVER.
IMMUNITY AND A TARP.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
RUSSELL, YOU THREW A PIECE OF
THE PUZZLE AT THE END.
WHAT IS THE FRUSTRATION?
I'M PISSED OFF.
I'M SICK OF THIS.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I CAN'T HANDLE THIS.
EITHER GO HARD OR GO HOME.
FORGET THESE OTHER STUPID
TALKING TRIBES.
THEY CAN'T BEAT US.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE ABLE TO BEAT
US.
Jeff: AND YET THEY HAVE
TWICE.
THAT'S BECAUSE THESE FOLKS
HAVEN'T DECIDED THAT THEY ARE
UNBEATABLE, THAT THEY CAN DO
THIS.
THEY HAVE TO GET THEIR HEADS OUT
OF THEIR BUTT OR GO HOME.
Jeff: SOMEBODY GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT OF YOUR TRIBE.
AT LEAST WE WERE CLOSE.
CLOSE DOESN'T KEEP US OUT OF
TRIBAL.
SO WE GO TO THE CHALLENGE
TODAY, AND ONCE AGAIN, WE LOST.
20-YEAR-OLD ANGIE, BEAUTY QUEEN,
SHE'S, LIKE, "I DON'T THINK I
CAN DO THIS."
AND THEN HERE'S ROXY SAYING,
"NOT ME.
I HAVE NOT HAD ENOUGH WATER TO
DRINK TODAY."
AND I JUST LOST IT.
GUYS, I'M SORRY.
CURSING DOESN'T HELP ANYTHING.
THE EMOTIONS WERE RUNNING
HIGH.
ROX 18 HAS BEEN EXTREMELY
SUCCESSFUL AT MAKING HERSELF A
TARGET FOR GETTING HER HEAD
CHOPPED OFF.
BUT I NEED ROXY.
EVERY TIME SOMETHING HAPPENS IN
CAMP, IF SHE'S AROUND, I KNOW
ABOUT IT.
SHE WAS THE ONE THAT TOLD ME
ABOUT MALCOLM AND ANGIE.
THOSE TWO HAVE LINKED UP, AND
I'M THE ONE WITH THE LARGEST
TARGET ON MY BACK, SO IF ROX 18
GOES, I'M, LIKE, SCREWED.
IT'S A PUBLIC EMBARRASSMENT
IF YOU ASK ME.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
GIRLFRIEND'S ON THE FLOOR,
PASSED OUT.
SHE WAS ON THE FLOOR.
YOU'RE PREACHING TO THE CHOIR
ON THAT, SISTER.
THIS IS WHY COMPANIES DON'T
LIKE FLATTERRIZATION.
IT SPOILS A GROUP.
BUT THEY DON'T LISTEN TO ME.
MALCOLM AND ANGIE ARE TOO BUSY
BEING UP EACH OTHER'S BUTT AND
IT'S FRUSTRATING BECAUSE HE
DOESN'T BRING ANYTHING TO THE
TEAM.
SHE PLAYS A CHEAP GAME.
I CAN RESPECT PEOPLE WHO DO GOOD
GAMES, WHERE THEY'RE SCHEMING.
THAT ONE OVER THERE WHO DOESN'T
HAVE ANY SKILL AT ALL.
JUST SHOW THE BOOBS.
SOMEBODY WILL FALL FOR IT.
IT'S LIKE MISS AMERICA ALL DAY
LONG, AND IT'S ANNOYING.
BOTTOM LINE, ANGIE NEEDS TO GO.
NOT JUST BECAUSE SHEETS WEAKEST
LINK BUT HER RELATIONSHIP WITH
MALCOLM IS NOT GOOD.
SHE SHOULD HAVE WENT FIRST.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
WE'RE GONNA BE CALLED OUT.
FOR WHAT?
SLEEPING SITUATION.
WELL, WHAT'S SHE GONNA SAY?
I DON'T KNOW--
WE NEED TO VOTE ANGIE OUT.
THAT'S WHAT SHE'S SAYING.
SHE IS?
WHAT ELSE WOULD SHE SAY?
I'M SURE, YEAH.
IT'S THE ONLY OPTION.
I THOUGHT IT WAS A DONE DEAL
THAT ROXY'S GOING HOME.
THE GIRL IS DOING NOTHING AROUND
CAMP, AND SHE JUST ISN'T HELPFUL
WITH ANYTHING, BUT THE GIRL
STILL HAS A LITTLE FIGHT IN HER.
SHE CHATTED UP RUSSELL AND FOR A
GOOD LONG WHILE.
I KNOW I SHOULDN'T BE CUDDLING
WITH ANGIE.
BUT IT'S COLD AT NIGHT AND I
SKOOCH OVER AND AN ARM COMES AND
MAYBE A LEG, AND THEN I'M, "ALL
RIGHT."
IT'S ONLY FLESH AND BLOOD.
A GOOD-LOOKING BLOND GIRL
THROWING THROES HER ARM AND LEG
OVER ME I'M NOT GOING TO PUSH
HER AWAY BUT NOW I'M NERVOUS
THAT MIGHT COME BACK TO BITE ME.
WOW, DID I GET AN EARFUL.
SHE DOES HAVE A LITTLE
SURVIVAL INSTINCT.
SHE HAD PLENTY OF INTERESTING
THINGS TO SAY.
MY CONCERN IS ANGIE IS TRYING TO
COME OFF AS THIS SWEET LITTLE
MISS AMERICA YOU TAW THING.
BUT ANGIE ISN'T AS INNOCENT A
PLAYER.
WHO'S TO SAY WE DON'T LOSE
ANOTHER DAMN CHALLENGE.
HOW DO I THINK THAT'S GOING TO
CUT?
SHE CHOPS MY HEAD OFF.
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
IF ROXAN GOES, I'M NEXT.
AT THIS POINT, ROXY AND
RUSSELL ARE DEFINITELY ALIGNED,
AND I KNOW MALCOLM AND ANGIE ARE
ALIGNED.
AND I'M CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
ALL THIS.
I CAN'T PUT MY FINGER ON IT, BUT
THERE IS SOMETHING JUST ABOUT
ROXY THAT I JUST DON'T TRUST.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, EVEN
THOUGH I'VE GOT MY ALLIANCE WITH
MALCOLM, I MEAN, IF SOMEBODY'S
SNUGGLING AND I'M THE ODD ONE
OUT, I'M ON THE BOTTOM.
I MEAN, AND I DON'T WANT TO BE
ON THE BOTTOM.
MAYBE I GIVE MALCOLM TOO MUCH
CREDIT IN THE SENSE OF PLEASE BE
A STRATEGIC PLAYER.
PLEASE DON'T BE BLINDED BY THE
HEADLIGHTS.
PLEASE.
THE PROBLEM IS, THERE'S PROS AND
CONS TO KEEPING BOTH BUT I'VE
GOT TO DO WHAT'S BEST FOR ME SO
AGAIN I FEEL PRETTY SURE ABOUT
WHAT MY VOTE'S GOING TO BE BUT
IT'S A LONG WAY TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, AND I'LL HAVE TO FIGURE
IT OUT.
Jeff: SO, RUSSELL, A LOT OF
EMOTION AT THE END OF THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
JEFF, I'M INTENSE ABOUT THIS.
THIS MEANS A LOT.
I DON'T COME HERE TO JUST
DILLYDALLY AND BE CUTE AND ALL
THAT KIND OF STUFF.
I COME HERE TO KICK BUTT.
Jeff: DENISE, IT WAS NOT
ONLY BOISTEROUS.
IT WAS A LITTLE ACCUSATORY.
"THIS TRIBE NEEDS TO GET IT
TOGETHER."
IT FELT REALLY ACCUSATORY BUT
AT THE SAME TIME I GET IT.
I DO.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING OUR TAIL OFFS
AROUND CAMP.
WE WANTED TO BE PREPARED TO GO
IN AND IT SUCKS.
Jeff: ROXY, FINISH THIS
SENTENCE FOR ME, "IF THERE'S ONE
THING I COULD CHANGE ABOUT THIS
TRIBE IT WOULD BE...."
THAT THEY WON'T INVEST 75% OF
THEIR ENERGY INTO BEING
WORKHORSES AROUND CAMP.
Jeff: YOU'RE SAYING THEY
PUT TOO MUCH ENERGY AT CAMP.
ABSOLUTELY.
I FEEL LIKE TO COME BACK AND A
SECOND CHALLENGE THAT WE LOST
AND IT'S JUST BACK TO WORK.
LIKE, THAT'S AWKWARD.
Jeff: DENISE, YOU'RE
NODDING YOUR HEAD LIKE THAT
MAKES SENSE.
NO.
IF WE WANT TO BE STRONG FOR
CHALLENGES, WE NEED TO GET WOOD.
WE NEED TO GET THAT FIRE GOING.
WE HAVE TO WORK.
THAT'S REALLY WHAT'S GOING ON.
Jeff: ANGIE, FINISH THAT
SAME SENTENCE, "IF I COULD
CHANGE ONE THING ABOUT THIS
TRIBE..."
THAT WE COULD HAVE COOKIES.
WOW.
Jeff: MALCOLM, ANGIE, FAIR
ANSWER, SAYS KEEKS WOULD BE
GOOD.
UH, YOU KNOW, THE STOMACH
RUMBLING IS SOMETHING WE'RE ALL
GETTING USED TO SO I CAN
UNDERSTAND THE KEEK RESPONSE --
WAIT A SECOND.
REALLY?
I'M TRYING TO BE NICE.
Jeff: IN A GAME FOR A
MILLION DOLLARS, ONE OF YOUR
TRIBEMATES SAYS COOKIES WOULD BE
GOOD.
AND YOU SAY, YEAH, YOU KNOW,
THEY WOULD BE.
IT'S NOT MY ANSWER BUT IT'S
BEEN HARD ON THE GIRLS
EMOTIONALLY AND PHYSICALLY.
I'M NOT SAYING IT'S A PHENOMENAL
ANSWER.
Jeff: RUSSELL, IS THIS WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, YOU GUYS
HAVE LOST TWO CHALLENGES IN A
ROW, AND ONE OF YOUR TRIBE MATES
SAYS IF I COULD CHANGE ANYTHING,
COOKIES.
I MEAN, JEFF, SHE'S A
WONDERFUL YOUNG LADY, AND I GIVE
HER MAD PROPS BUT THIS IS JUST
NEW TO HER.
SO THE THING IS YOU HAVE TO
LEAVE EVERYTHING OUT THERE EVERY
CHALLENGE.
AND YOU HAVE TO BE COMPLETELY
ABOUT ACTION.
Jeff: ROXY, DO YOU SEE
FRIENDSHIPS STARTING TO FORM IN
THIS LITTLE CLUSTER OF PEOPLE?
FRIENDSHIPS, ABSOLUTELY.
OTHER THINGS AS WELL.
I MEAN, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON BETWEEN ANGIE
AND MALCOLM, BUT IT'S WAY BEYOND
JUST AN ALLIANCE.
Jeff: BEYOND AN ALLIANCE.
ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: AS IN ROMANCE.
PROBABLY.
WHAT'S UP?
Jeff: I DIDN'T EVEN SAY
ANYTHING, MALCOLM.
DID YOU THAT LOOK.
I ALREADY GOT IT FIGURED OUT.
Jeff: SO IS THERE A LITTLE
SOMETHING BETWEEN YOU AND ANGIE?
NO, BUT WE SLEEP NEXT
TOGETHER AT NIGHT, AND IT GETS
COLD, SO THERE'S, YOU KNOW,
MUTUAL WARMTH.
Jeff: WHAT DO YOU THINK
ROXY'S PICKING UP ON?
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY ELSE IN
THE SHELTER IS, UH--
SNUGGLING.
AS CLOSE AS WE ARE.
SNUGGLING, THERE'S A GOOD
WORD FOR IT.
IT DOES STAND OUT A LITTLE BIT.
IT'S NOT ROMANTIC AT ALL.
SHE'S LIKE A LITTLE SISTER TO
ME.
REALLY.
CREEPY.
Jeff: WHAT WAS THAT ROXY.
IF I HAD A BROTHER I WOULDN'T BE
CUDDLING WITH THEM.
I MEAN, LOOK AT ANGIE.
THIS IS AN ATTRACTIVE GIRL.
IT JUST SO HAPPENS THAT THAT'S
THE PERSON YOU FEEL LIKE IS YOUR
LITTLE SISTER.
OKAY.
Jeff: WHY DOES IT BOTH
BOTHER YOU.
IT BOTHERED ME ON DAY ONE.
TO ME IT WAS LIKE A BOOBY TRAP--
SORRY-- LITERALLY.
WHAT, WHAT.
I'M SORRY THAT I'M COLD.
I'M FREEZING.
YEAH, YOU WERE FREEZING?
I WOULD CUDDLE WITH YOU,
BUT--
NO, NO, I'M GOOD.
BUT DON'T.
YEAH.
Jeff: RUSSELL, TWO PEOPLE,
EVEN THE APPEARANCE OF BEING
TOGETHER IN A GROUP OF FIVE SOON
TO BE FOUR, THAT'S HALF THE
TRIBE.
OH, ABSOLUTE.
YOU KNOW, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
RELATIONSHIPS, YOU KNOW, THAT'S
THE TIGHTEST ALLIANCE YOU COULD
EVER HAVE IN "SURVIVOR."
Jeff: SO, ANGIE, DO YOU
UNDERSTAND THAT?
I DO.
Jeff: THE MERE MENTION OF
BEING WITH SOMEBODY ELSE IS
ENOUGH TO GET YOU VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
UH-HUH.
Jeff: AND ROXY JUST THREW
THAT CLOUD OF SUSPICION OVER THE
BOTH OF YOU.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S HER OPINION.
AND SHE CAN HAVE THAT.
Jeff: LET'S GET REAL HONEST
HERE, ANGIE.
LET'S WAKE UP.
HERE'S WHAT'S HAPPENING.
THERE'S SUSPICION.
MALCOLM, YOU'RE UNDER THE SAME
BUS.
WHAT IF YOU TWO ARE LINKED?
YEAH, IT'S ALL OUT THERE BUT,
YOU KNOW, I'M TIGHT WHAT A GROUP
OF PEOPLE AND HOPEFULLY THEY
UNDERSTAND IT AND THEY'LL TAKE
IT FOR WHAT IT IS NOT FOR WHAT
SOMEBODY IS TRYING TO TWIST IT
TO BE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF?
ALL I HAVE TO SAY IS A PAIR IN
THIS GAME IS VERY DANGEROUS.
SO IF THERE'S EVEN A 60% CHANCE
THAT THERE'S MORE THERE BETWEEN
ANGIE AND MALCOLM, THEN GOOD
LUCK TO THE REST OF YOU IF YOU
CHOOSE HER OVER ME.
Jeff: WITH THAT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
MALCOLM, YOU'RE UP.
I HAVE TO CALL A SPADE A
SPADE.
IF YOU WANT TO PRETEND LIKE IT'S
SOMETHING ELSE, GO AHEAD.
GOD BLESS YOU AND SHHOM.
I CAN'T STAND YOU.
AND I WON'T MISS YOU.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ROXY.
ANGIE.
ONE VOTE ROXY, ONE VOTE ANGIE.
ROXY.
THAT'S TWO VOTES ROXY, ONE VOTE
ANGIE.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES," ROXY.
THAT'S THREE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ROXY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME TO GO.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS TOMORROW
IS ANOTHER DAY AND FORTUNES IN
THIS GAME CAN CHANGE VERY FAST.
KEEP YOUR HEADS UP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": 7.
LISA SCRAMBLES.
WOULD YOU BE OKAY IF WE HAD
TO GET RID OF MIKE.
JUST TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
EVERY DAY I HAVE TO PLAY THE
HAND I'M LEFT.
RUSSELL SLIDES.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S GOD'S
PLAN FOR ME TO BE HERE.
Jeff: AND SKUPIN PUTS
EVERYTHING ON THE LINE.
SKUPIN BLEEDING FROM THE FACE!
IT'S BEEN SIX DAYS, BUT IT'S
BEEN SIX LONG DAYS.
I THINK THAT THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN ANGIE AND MALCOLM WILL
IMPACT THE GAME OF DENISE AND
RUSSELL.
AT THIS POINT, THERE'S NO PLACE
TO HIDE, AND EVERY SINGLE ONE OF
THEM BETTER BE SUPER STAR
OLYMPIANS.
I HAVE SOME GOOD TIES TO THAT
GROUP BUT IF THEY BELIEVE THEY
MADE THE BEST DECISION MAY BE