>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
>> A PAIR FROM THE BEGINNING,
MALCOLM AND DID NIECE WERE THE
LAST REMAINING MEMBERS OF MATS.
>> HE'S YOUNG BUT HE'S WISE.
WE JUST CLICKED.
>> Jeff: THEIR MOOD IMPROVED
WHEN THEY FOUND THE IDOL.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: UNTIL A SUDDEN CHANGE
IN THE GAME SPLIT THEM UP.
MALCOLM, DENISE, YOU CAN DROP
YOUR BUFFS.
MALCOLM AND HIS IDOL WERE SENT
TO TANDANG, WINNING CHALLENGE
AFTER CHALLENGE.
TANDANG WINS REWARD!
TANDANG WINS IMMUNITY.
>> I'M LIKE THE STUD FOOTBALL
PLAYER.
EVERYONE IS PULLING ME ASIDE
SAYING, "I'LL BE YOUR BEST
FRIEND."
>> BENIECE HAD YET TO TASTE VICT
GEE.
>> EVERY STEP IS AN OPPORTUNITY
TO TURN THINGS AROUND.
>> Jeff: AT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE, TANDANG'S WINNING
STREAK CAME TO AN END WHEN
SKUPIN AND R.C. CONVINCED THEIR
TRIBE TO FORFEIT THE VICTORY FOR
THE REST OF KALABAW'S RICE.
>> DO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
DO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO, MIKE.
>> Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE IS
OVER.
REWARD GOES TO KALABAW.
>> GOOD JOB, TANDANG.
>> Jeff: BACK AT CAMP, ABOO,
PETE, AND ARTIS WERE ALL BUT
SATISFIES.
>> IT'S GONNA BE ONE OF THE
DUMBEST MOMENTOF SURVIVOR, GIG
OUT A PRIZE LIKE THAT.
>> Jeff: VELLIFYING FOR SKUPIN
AND R.C. FOR GIVING UP REWARD.
>> WE HAVE A MEMBER OF OUR TRIBE
WHO HAS DONE ABSOLUTE NOTHING
FOR OUR TRIBE.
SHUT UP.
IT IS NOT A GOOD THING.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, MALCOLM
SINGLEHANDEDLY CAUGHT THE
VICTORY FOR TANDANG.
TANDANG WINS IMMUNITY!
WHILE KATIE CONTINUED TO BE A
LIABILITY.
>> I HATE TO LOSE KATIE.
AT LEAST WITH DENISE WE HAVE A
CHANCE OF WINNING.
>> HE HAD ANOTHER IDEAS, TARGETS
PENNER.
>> HE HAS TO MAKE SURE HE
DOESN'T KNOW IT'S COMING.
THE HARD DECISION IS VOTING
JONATHAN OUT.
I MIGHT NEED HIM TO GET ME
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: 11 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL
BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> A LONG NIGHT.
>> LONG NIGHT.
>> DENISE, WE HAVE TO YOU A
BREAK FROM THIS TRIBAL NONSENSE.
>> I KNOW.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK.
>> YOU'VE BEEN TO EVERY DAMN
ONE.
>> SEECIALLY.
SKEW THAT.
>> COMING BACK FROM THE SIXTH
TRIBAL COUNCIL IN A ROW.
I'M GLAD I'M BACK.
IT'S LIKE DEJA VU.
IT'S ONE AFTER THE OTHER.
I AM WONDER AM I CURSED?
HAVE I BROUGHT SOMETHING TO THIS
TRIBE.
>> I WAS SURPRISED YOU WROTE MY
NAME.
DID SHE CATCH WIND OF IT AND
VOTED FOR ME?
>> SHE WAS PISSED OFF AT SOME
REASON.
SHE WANTED YOU OUT.
AND I COULDN'T CONVINCE HER
OTHERWISE, SO I JUST LET HER RUN
WITH IT TRIBAL TONIGHT WAS
CHAOTIC.
BOY, I WAS SO CLOSE TO LETTING
PENNER GOING BUT I'M THINKING
PENNER IS GOING TO HELP ME OUT.
I'M HOPING I MADE THE RIGHT
CHOICE.
WE'RE TWO GUYS TAKING A SHOT IN
THE DARK AT EACH OTHER, AND
THERE'S GOING TO COME A TIME AND
A PLACE AND I HOPE I CAN GET TO
HIM FIRST BEFORE HE GETS TO ME.
>> SHE WAS READY TO THROW
ANYBODY UNDER THE BUS OKAY, SO
IT WAS ME.
WELL, THANKS, GUYS, FOR NOT
VOTING WITH HER.
>> YUP.
>> I THINK JEFF AND I HAVE BUILT
A TRUST WITH EACH OTHER.
BUT I WAS REALLY SURPRISED TO
SEE MY NAME.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN.
I JUST FORGET THAT OTHER PEOPLE
ARE LYING.
IT'S ALWAYS MY PROBLEM.
IT WAS A GOOD WAKE-UP CALL.
DO I HAVE TO KEEP MY EYES AND
EARS OPEN AS WE MOVE FORWARD?
OF COURSE.
I'D BE RIDICULOUSLY STUPID NOT
TO.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> REALLY?
( LAUGHTER ).
>> I FELL IN THE FIRE TODAY,
THIS FAR INTO THE GAME, 24
SEASONS AGO.
SO I NO LONGER HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE.
WE'RE NOW IN ALL NEW TERRITORY
FOR ALL OF US.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE NEED.
WE NEED ONE OF THOSE.
>> SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT IS THIS?
>> IT'S TURNING INTO OUR COVE?
>> IS IT?
WE WERE JUST LYING AROUND
THINKING IT WAS GOING TO BE A
LONG DAY, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
WE SAW THIS BOAT, AND WE THOUGHT
IS IT COMING INTO THE COVE?
IT'S COMING INTO THE COVE, IT'S
COMING!
>> WELCOME.
>> AND THEN WE FOUND OUT THE
BEST NEWS THAT WE'VE HEARD SINCE
DAY ONE.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
THE TRIBES ARE MERGING!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> THIS BOAT HAS BEEN SENT TO
TAKE YOU TO YOUR NEW HOMES.
THE DRIVER HAS BEEN INSTRUCTED
TO GIVE YOU 10 MINUTES.
>> TO COLLECT WHATEVER YOU FEEL
YOU NEED TO START YOUR NEW
WORLD.
YOUR TIME STARTS NOW.
>> WHEN YOU ONLY HAVE 10 MINUTE
TO GATHER UP EVERYTHING YOU
HAVE, EVERYTHING IS LIKE GOLD.
MAKING SURE THAT I DON'T HAVE
SOCKS HANGING OUT ON A LINE
SOMEWHERE AND SHOES HIDDEN
UNDERNEATH THE RAFT SOMEWHERE.
THAT'S PRIORITY ONE.
>> WE HAVE TO GET THE TARP DOWN.
>> OUR BOTTLES OF WATER.
>> I BURIED MY IDOL THE FIRST
DAY I GOT HERE.
NOW WE HAVE 10 MINUTES SO I HAVE
TO DIG IT UP AGAIN.
>> IT'S REALLY HEAVY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
THE TRIBES ARE MERGING!
( CHEERS )
THIS BOAT HAS BEEN SENT TO TAKE
YOU TO YOUR NEW HOME.
IT'S A NEW LIFE LINE FOR US.
THERE ARE FOUR OF US, THERE ARE
SEVEN OF THEM.
WE'RE HOPING THERE'S DESCENT
OVER THERE AND WE CAN PICK ONE
OR TWO PEOPLE TO COME OVER TO
OUR SIDE TO USE FOR A WHILE AND
THUT THEM OFF IF WE CAN.
YEAH!
OKAY.
WATER BOTTLES.
TARPS.
>> CLOTHES.
WHAT ABOUT OUR KINDLING?
>> WE'RE GOING TO STAY FOUR
STRONG.
WE NEED TWO TO SHIFT THAT
BALANCE AND HAVE A MAJORITY.
SO MY PLAN IS TO STICK WITH THE
ALLIANCE I'VE GOT GOING WITH
KALABAW, BUT AT THE SAME TIME I
TRULY WOULD LIKE TO BE BACK TO
MY ORIGINAL ALLIANCE WITH
MALCOLM.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS )
>> HI.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU!
>> GUYS, UNLOAD EVERYTHING
FIRST.
>> I'M DENISE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> I BELIEVE THAT A VETERAN
PLAYER SHOULDN'T BE WINNING THIS
GAME.
PENNER'S ALWAYS BEEN MY PRIORITY
SINCE AT A ONE.
AND NOW THAT I'M ON A TEAM WITH
PENNER AND SKUPIN, I'VE GOT TWO
PRIORITIES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> CHEERS!
>> TO OUR NEW TRIBE.
>> IT WAS A GOOD INTRODUCTION.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE ANYBODY
KNOWS WHO I AM, WHICH IS I THINK
A GOOD THING.
>> WHERE IS EVERYONE FROM?
>> I LIVE IN TEXAS.
I HAVE A RANCH.
>> I KNEW IT!
>> AND I AM A MOTORCYCLE DEALER.
>> OH!
>> AS LONG AS THEY DON'T TALK
ABOUT BASEBALL, MAYBE I'M SAFE.
>> CAN I HAVE SOME MORE OF THAT
WINE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE HAVE FOUR BOTTLES.
>> AND WE HAVE BREAD, TOO,
RIGHT?
>> WE DO.
>> CAN I HAVE SOME OF THAT MEAT?
>> YEAH.
IT'S VERY HARD TO CUT.
>> I'M DOWN FOR CHEWING IT.
>> START TOSSING IT IN YOUR
MOUTH.
>> THE FEAST WAS AMAZING.
THERE WAS MORE FOOD THAN YOU
COULD EVER EAT.
THE WINE WAS AWESOME.
THE TRIBE AND TENSION WHEN HE
FIRST LAND ON THE ISLAND WAS GO
TANDANG STRONG.
SKUPIN DOESN'T HAVE A BRAIN OF
HIS OWN AND DOES WHARF R.C.
TELLS HIM TO DO.
>> I HAVE SEVEN KIDS, MARRIED.
>> SEVEN KIDS AND MARRIED.
>> I'M MARRIED.
LIKE I NEVER MADE THE MERGE
BEFORE.
THEY MERGED IN AUSTRALIA THE DAY
AFTER I WAS MED EVACKED.
SO THIS IS KIND OF COOL.
AND MERGING WITH NUMBERS, EVEN
BETTER.
>> WHAT'S THE RANGE IN AGE?
>> COLLEGE, HOLLY, MIDDLE
SCHOOL, ELEMENTARY.
I NEVER STOPPED HAVING THEM.
>> BUT I NOTICED PETE AND ABEERK
THE POWER ALLIANCE ON OUR TRIBE,
BEING A LITTLE QUIET BECAUSE
THEY HAVEN'T HAD AN ALLEGIANCE
IN WEEKS TO R.C. AND I.
AND SO WE'RE REALLY FREE AGENTS.
SO BEING A FREE AGENT MEANS YOU
GET TO CHOOSE YOUR TEAM.
IT JUST TAKES TWO.
>> I THINK DENISE WILL TALK TO
ME A LITTLE BIT MORE JUST
BECAUSE OF THE SWIMMING
CONNECTION.
>> YOU SHOULD ACT AS A SPY THEN
TO GET INFORMATION.
>> I KNOW, BUT JUST AS MUCH YOU
WANT ME TO GET INFORMATION I
WORRY BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, WE
AREN'T ONING, BIG, HAPPY FAMILY.
WE CAN PRETEND TO BE ALL WE
WANT, BUT WE HAVEN'T FOR 17
DAYS.
>> IT'S TRUE.
SHELTER YOU MIGHT AS WELL SAY
HI.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF BAMBOO.
WE CAN'T MAKE SOMETHING OUT OF
THAT, THEN, GET US BACK TO THE
COUCH.
>> ON THE NEW BEACH, I THOUGHT,
WELL, THE GUYS ARE MAKE THE
SHELTER.
I'LL JUST HANG EVERYBODY'S
CLOTHES OUT AND GET THEM SOME
SUN SO WE DON'T GO TO SLEEP WITH
WET CLOTHES.
AND THEN I PICKED UP MALCOLM'S
BAG, AND I TOOK HIS FLANNEL
SHIRT OUT, AND I TOOK HIS
BATHING SUIT OUT AND I WAS
LOOKING IN THERE AND I FELT
SOMETHING.
I'VE DISCOVERED HE HAD THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IN HIS BAG
WHICH TOTALLY SHOCKED ME.
>> ALL THE CLOTHES ARE LAID OUT.
AND IT WAS WRAPPED UP.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND WAS LIKE--
>> LISA.
LISA DID THAT.
>> I NEED TO TALK TO LISA RIGHT
NOW.
>> NO, BECAUSE -- OF NO, BECAUSE
LISA WAS PULLING OUT CLOTHES.
>> I WAS GOING TO CHANGE CLOTHES
AND HIDE THE IDOL.
I THOUGHT AN HOUR WOULD BE A
SAFE AMOUNT OF TIME ASSUMING
PEOPLE WOULD BE EATING AND
DRINKING AND KNOWING EACH OTHER.
PAECIAL THE ESTROGEN CLICKED IN
AND WE HAD TO HAVE OUR CLOTHES
CLEANED.
>> OH, CRAP, MALCOLM.
>> NOW I HAVE TO PIN DOWN SWEET
OLD LISA WHO I THINK, OUT OF THE
GOODNESS OF HER HEART, IS TRYING
TO DRY MY CLOTHES.
I GET HER ALONE.
I DON'T SAY A WORD.
I JUST LOOK AT HER.
>> LET ME TELL YOU THIS.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO TELL
ME?
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
>> I KNEW IT.
I PROMISE I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M LIKE YOU'VE GOT TO BE
KIDDING ME.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
HONESTLY, I WAS JUST TRYING TO
AIR OUT EVERYBODY'S LAUNDRY.
>> I SAID SHE'S SO SWEET.
SHE WAS JUST TRYING TO BE NICE.
>> I REALLY WAS.
>> I WON'T TELL ANYBODY.
>> IT'S ME, YOU, AND DENISE
KNOW.
ME AND DENISE HAVE BEEN SUPER
TIGHT SINCE THE BEGINNING.
>> OKAY.
>> AND YOU'RE MY NEW MOMMA AND
NOOSE JUST HOW IT'S GOING TO BE.
IT'S THE THREE OF US TO THE END.
NOBODY KNOWS ABOUT IT.
>> OKAY.
>> HALLELUJAH.
THE CHURCH LADY FOUND IT, WHO
HOPEFULLY HAS A HEART.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, NOW I'M
LOCKED INTO THIS INVOLUNTARY
ALLIANCE WITH LISA AND
DENEETION.
IT'S LITERALLY THE TWO PEOPLE
I'M NOT CONFIDENT I CAN BEAT IN
THE FINAL THREE.
JUST BECAUSE THEY'RE NICE, BUT
THE WHOLE DYNAMICS COULD SHIFT,
AND THE ENTIRE CAMP IS GOING
CRAZY WITH SCRAMBLING.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> YOU GAVE ME A HEART ATTACK.
>> MALCOLM PROMISED FINAL THREE
WITH ME AND DENISE, AND THAT'S
REALLY NICE.
BUT YOU KIND OF HAVE TO TAKE ALL
THAT WITH A GRAIN OF SALT.
I'M NOT THE ONLY ACTOR ON THIS
ISLAND.
SO I COULD BE BEING PLAYED.
>> OH, THAT'S AMAZING.
>> I HAVEN'T HAD TO DEAL WITH
IT.
>> THEY'RE TOO YOUNG.
>> I KNOW.
I'M SHOCKED.
>> YOU KNOW, THIS IS JUST SO
MUCH FUN TO JUST GET TO BE ME.
>> YEAH.
>> SO PENNER IS AWARE OF MY PAST
AS A CHILD STAR.
BUT WE DIDN'T TALK STRATEGY.
AND IF WE WEREN'T ON THIS
ISLAND, WE WOULD HAVE A REALLY
GREAT TIME OVER LUNCH, JUST
TALKING ABOUT EACH OTHER'S
LIVES.
AND IF YOU HAVE THAT KIND OF
CONNECTION, THAT IS VALUABLE,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU DO END UP
ALIGNED LATER ON DOWN THE ROAD.
>> YOU JUST NEVER, EVER REALLY
KNOW IF SOMEBODY LIKES YOU FOR
YOU AND TO HAVE THESE
FRIENDSHIPS ALREADY THAT REALLY
ARE TOTALLY BASED ON LIKING ME
FOR ME.
IS VERY HEALING IN A REALLY DEEP
WAY.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T ANTICIPATE
THAT THAT WOULD BE SOMETHING I
WOULD TAKE FROM THIS.
>> LISA HAD BEEN ON "FACT OF
LIFE," BUT NOW AS WITH MANY,
MANY FORMER ACTORS YOU GET OLDER
AND SO YOU DO OTHER THINGS WITH
YOUR LIFE.
LISA IS KIND OF A COOL LADY.
I THINK SHE COULD ACTUALLY GO
PRETTY FAR AS AN UNDER-THE-RADAR
NONTHREATENING PERSON WHO COULD
FIND HERSELF SITTING AT A FINAL
THREE.
I BELIEVE THAT.
I WON'T BLOW YOUR COVER.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THEY'VE GOT THE NUMBERS NOW.
THEY COULD VOTE YOU AND I OUT IF
THEY WANT TO.
THAT'S MY FIRST CONCERN, FIRST
AND FOREMOST, IS JUST HOW TO
SURVIVE.
>> THE RETURNING PLAYER BULL'S
EYE.
>> THE QUESTION IS WHAT'S THE
SMARTEST MOVE?
I'M TRYING TO FIND FISSURES IN
THIS YELLOW TRIBE AND SKUPIN
SEEMS LIKE A COOL GUY.
SO I GOT TO HELP HIM FEEL AS
COMFORTABLE AS HE CAN ABOUT
SLITTING THE THROATS OF THE
PEOPLE HE SPENT 17 DAYS WITH.
YOU KNOW.
SO I'M TRYING TO DO THAT.
MY BACK'S AGAINST THE WALL, TOO.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M NEGOTIATING
WITH WHAT LITTLE I HAVE, WHICH
IS I GOT FOUR LOYAL PEOPLE.
I HAVE A REALLY SERIOUS BLOC.
IF YOU AND I CAN FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT, THAT WOULD BE
INCREDIBLE.
>> WHAT PERCENT ARE YOU ON
REALIGNMENT?
>> I MEAN, IT'S HARD.
>> GIVE A NUMBER RIGHT NOW.
JUST GIVE A NUMBER.
>> I'M 50-50.
THERE ARE A LOT OF DYNAMICS WORK
RIGHT NOW.
ME AND MIKE ARE SOILED, BUT WE
WOULD LIKE TO FEEL A LITTLE BIT
MORE SECURE.
>> I-- I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN
TRUST, WE'RE TANDANG, LET'S STAY
TANDANG, AND WHEN WE GET TO
SEVEN GAME ON.
>> GAME ON, I KNOW.
THE OLD TAN BANG TRIBE MADE IT
OBVIOUS ABOUT ME AND MIKE.
THEY OFTSIDES US BOTH FOR 17
DAYS.
SO PENNER CORRALLED HIS
THREESOME, AND I HAVE MIKE,
OBVIOUSLY, ON MY SIDE, SO THAT'S
SIX.
SO WHY WOULDN'T WE DO SOMETHING?
IF WE HAVE A POSSIBLE CHANCE TO
GO SOMEWHERE ELSE, JUDGE IN NOT.
>> WE NEED TO TAKE BABY STEPS.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
>> I DON'T WANT A VETERAN TO
WIN, AND I LIKE THEM--
>> EVEN GET RID OF MIKE, TOO.
>> GET PENNER OUT OF HERE.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO WIN.
>> HE'S HAD HIS CHANCE.
>> RIGHT.
I THINK HE HAS THE IDOL, THOUGH.
>> HE MAY.
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE IT.
IF HE'S GOT THE IDOL--
>> IT HAS TO BE A BLINDSIDE.
>> AND I'M GOING TO BE ABLE TO
HELP PLATOON THAT.
>> I KNOW PENNER'S GOT THE IDOL.
NOBODY ELSE KNOWS FOR SURE IF HE
DOES OR NOT, BUT I KNOW HE DOES.
AND I'LL JOIN ANY GANG AS LONG
AS I CAN GET PENNER OUT BEFORE I
GET OUT.
>> R.C. IS DANGEROUS.
>> SHE IS, ISN'T SHE?
>> SHE'S NUMBER ONE.
NUMBER TWO-- NUMBER TWO IS
EITHER PENNER OR MIKE.
>> AND I CAN GET CARTER, DENISE.
>> WHAT HAPPENS IF IT'S A
FOUR-FOUR TIE, WE PLAY IT FOUR
FOR R.C. AND WE PLAY IT FOUR FOR
PENNER.
>> FOUR-FOUR IS ALL YOU NEED.
>> PERFECT.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING.
>> LITTLE CLIQUE INSIDE OF
TANDANG IS OPERATING UNDER THE
ASSUMPTION THAT PENNER HAS AN
IDOL, BUT WE DON'T HAVE THE
NUMBERS WITHIN OUR OWN TRIBE TO
BE ABLE TO SPLIT THE VOTE AND
GET RID OF HIM SO WE HAVE TO
PULL IN JEFF, DENISE, AND
INDICATOR.
>> PENNER PLAYS THE IDOL, WE
FLUSH THE IDOL AND R.C. IS GONE.
>> WE COULD SPLIT THE VOTE
BETWEEN PENNER AND R.C.
PEB PENNER HAS AN IDOL HE HAS TO
PLAY TO SAVE HIMSELF AND R.C.
WILL GO HOME.
IF HE DOESN'T, WE'LL REVOTE AND
GET RID OF PENNER RIGHT NOW.
THE ONLY REAL WRINKLE IS IF THE
KALABAW, JEFF, CARTER, AND
DENISE, ARE GOING TO COME ALONG
WITH IT, AND GO ALONG LIKE
THEY'RE SAYING THEY WILL.
>> THE ONLY THING TOMORROW IS WE
CAN'T LET PENNER OR R.C. WIN
IMMUNITY.
>> ANYBODY ELSE CAN WIN IT.
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE FUN.
>> ALL RIGHT, COOL.
>> YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN THINKING
THE SAME WAY WE'VE BEEN THINKING
SINCE DAY ONE.
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
WILL TAKE BACK TRIBAL IMMUNITY.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NO MORE.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IS NOW WHAT
YOU COVET.
WITH THIS AROUND YOUR NECK, YOU
ARE SAFE IN THIS GAME.
WITHOUT IT, YOU ARE IN TROUBLE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
EACH GOING TO HOLD ON TO A ROPE
HANDLE ATTACHED TIE BUCKET.
EACH BUCKET IS FILLED WITH 25%
OF YOUR BODY WEIGHT.
AS THE CHALLENGE GOES ON, THAT
WEIGHT WILL BECOME TOO MUCH TO
BEAR.
THE ROPE WILL BEGIN TO UNSPOOL.
THE BUCKET WILL DROP.
WHEN YOUR BUCKET DROPS YOU'RE
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST MAN AND LAST WOMAN LEFT
STANDING WIN IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM
THE VOTE, GUARANTEED A ONE-IN-10
SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY IS IN
POSITION.
THIS CHALLENGE IS NOW OFFICIALLY
ON.
>> OH, THIS AIN'T GOING TO WORK.
>> Jeff: EACH BUCKET HAS 25%
OF YOUR BODY WEIGHT.
THAT IS A LOT OF WEIGHT TO HOLD
WITH ONLY YOUR WRISTS.
WITH A MILLION BUCKS ON THE
LINE, I'M GUESSING YOU GUYS WILL
GO AS DEEP AS YOU CAN INSIDE
YOURSELF.
>> Jeff: WOW.
JUST LIKE THAT SKUPIN IS OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
BAR SLIPS OUT OF HIS HANDS.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO 10.
>> IT'S GOING DOWN.
>> Jeff: PETE IS OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
THAT'S HOW QUICKLY IT CAN
HAPPEN.
YOU START TO SWEAT IN THIS VERY
INTENSE HEAT.
YOUR GRIP BECOMES WET.
IT'S WHY YOU HAVE TO
CONCENTRATE.
DO NOT DRIP.
REMIND YOURSELF EVERY FEW
SECONDS WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
SEND THAT SIGNAL FROM YOUR BRAIN
TO YOUR HAND TO HOLD ON.
PENNER DANGLING VERY CLOSE TO
THE END OF HIS ROPE.
IT HAS UNSPOOLD ALMOST ALL THE
WAY.
PENNER IS OUT OF THIS GAME AND
IN TROUBLE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: GLAD YOU'RE ON THE
SHOW, JONATHAN.
>> THANK YOU, BUDDY.
YOU TOO.
>> AH!
>> Jeff: LISA IS STARTING TO
SLIP A LITTLE BIT.
I'M GOING TO KEEP REMINDING YOU
TO KEEP YOUR CONCENTRATION.
LISA OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
MALCOLM IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE MEN AND
THREE WOMEN.
IT IS ABI, DENISE, AND RB
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
ARTIS, JEFF, AND CARTER FIGHTING
FOR IMMUNITY.
ONE MAN WILL GET IMMUNITY.
ONE WOMAN WILL GET IMMUNITY.
R.C. GOING TO WORK HERS BACK UP.
ABI STARTING TO SLIP A LITTLE
BIT.
DENISE LOOKS GOOD.
>> GOOD WORK, ABI.
GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: R.C. VERY CLOSE TO
THE END OF THER ROPE.
SHE'S STRUGGLING TO HANG ON.
SHE CAN'T DO IT.
R.C. IS NOW OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
ABI GETTING VERY CLOSE TO THE
END OF HER ROPE, AND SHE KNOWS
IT.
CAN'T DO IT ANYMORE.
AND WITH THAT, DENISE WINS
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY FOR THE
WOMEN.
DENISE SAFE AT TONIGHT'S VOTE.
>> NICE JOB.
AWESOME.
>> Jeff: ONE IMMUNITY NECKLACE
LEFT.
ARTIS, JEFF, AND CARTER.
ONE OF YOU WILL BE WEARING IT
SHORTLY.
THE OTHER TWO WILL BE GOING TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL EMPTY-HANDED.
THAT A WAY TO DIG.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ARTIS, WARRIOR.
>> YOU GUYS ARE DOING GREAT.
>> NICE TRY, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: ARTIS IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE AND WE ARE DOWN TO
TWO, JEFF AND CARTER, SIDE BY
SIDE.
>> WOW, KANSAS AND TEXAS, SIDE
BY SIDE.
>> Jeff: JEFF INCHES HIS BUCK
BACK UP.
ALMOST LIKE HE'S SHOWING CARTER,
"LOOK WHO YOU'RE DEALING WITH,
YOUNG 'UN."
>> COME ON, YOUNG BUCK.
>> Jeff: AND NO SOONER SAID
THAT THAN CARTER EVENS IT OUT.
>> GOOD JOB, CARTER.
YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING.
>> I SAID THAT'S FINE.
>> IT'S UP TO YOU.
>> Jeff: HOW'S IT GOING DOWN
HERE, JEFF AND CARTER.
>> HAVING THE NECKLACE ON
TONIGHT WOULD BE SWEET.
AND, YEAH, I JUST WANT TO WIN.
>> Jeff: AND JUST LIKE THAT,
JEFF DROPS OUT.
CARTER WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
>> GO, CARTER!
>> Jeff: CARTER AND DENISE
BOTH WILL HAVE IMMUNITY AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> JEFF, I KNOW YOU COULD HAVE
KEPT GOING.
>> THAT WAS WAR.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE HERE FOR.
>> Jeff: DENISE, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
>> THAT'S THE FIRST TIME SHE'S
HAD IMMUNITY.
>> IT MIGHT BE HEAVIER THAN HER.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: DENISE, SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SLIDE RIGHT OVER HERE.
CARTER, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
>> GO, CARTER!
>> Jeff: CARTER, SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, TONIGHT
YOUR SHOT AT THE MILLION DOLLARS
WILL COME TO AN END.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> I'M ACSTATIC THAT PEB PENNER
AND R.C. DIDN'T EVEN COME CLOSE
TO WINNING IMMUNITY BECAUSE
WE'RE GOING TO SPLIT THE VOTE
BETWEEN PENNER AND R.C., AND IF
PENNER PLAYS THE IDOL, R.C. GOES
HOME.
IF PENNER DOESN'T PLAY THE IDOL,
HE'LL GO HOME WITH THE IDOL.
SO FAR.
NO, I DIDN'T WIN IMMUNITY, BUT
WE SORT OF HAVE THIS VERY COOR
SIX IN PLACE RIGHT NOW.
ME AND MIKE ARE SOLID, AND WE
ARE DEFINITELY WITH KALABAW.
WITH US SIX WE ARE IN THE
MAJORITY.
>> I NEVER HAVE EVER FELT
THREATENED BEFORE, AND TONIGHT,
RETURNING PLAYERS ARE A MAJOR
THREAT.
LIKE, MY REPUTATION IS PRETTY
COMPETITIVE.
MY REPUTATION ISN'T BEING LOYAL
TO A TRIBE THAT HASN'T BEEN
LOYAL TO ME.
THERE ISN'T ANYBODY THAT WOULD
THINK THAT I WOULD GO DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
I CAN'T PLAY THE GAME WITH THEM.
>> YEAH.
BIGGEST HANG-UP I HAVE OF ALL
THIS IS I DON'T WANT TO LET
PENNER BEAT ME OUT IN THIS GAME.
IT'S AND YOU PENNER GET
TOGETHER, AND THERE ARE TWO
VETERAN GUYS.
LET'S TAKE IT TO THE END.
SO WE GET SCREWED.
THAT'S THE OWNING THING I WORRY
ABOUT.
>> I CAN TELL WITH YOU INTEGRITY
THAT I WOULD FOLLOW YOU GUYS.
IT JUST TAKES TWO PEOPLE FROM
TANDANG TO REALIGN WITH THE
KALABAW TRIBE.
THEN THEY WOULD BE SIX STRONG.
UNLESS GOD HIMSELF APPEARS LIVE
BEFORE ME AND SPEAKS TO ME, I
CANNOT FOLLOW PETE, ARTIS, AND
ABI, AS LONG AS I HAVE SOME
ASSURANCE THAT JEFF AND CARTER
AREN'T GOING TO SWITCH OVER TO
THE OLD TANDANG TRIBE.
BECAUSE IF R.C. AND I GO THIS
WAY, AND JEFF AND CARTER GO THIS
WAY, WHAT HAPPENS?
NOTHING GOT GAINED.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO, MAN?
SO THE ONLY THING I CAN THINK OF
HERE IS YOU AND I HOLD THE KEY.
>> YUP.
>> SO I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> WELL, IT'S JONATHAN, SKUPIN,
R.C., DENISE, YOU, ME, THAT'S
ALL WE NEED.
>> YUP.
SIX.
WE JUST NEED SIX.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU THINK WE COULD GET
FARTHER WITH SKUPIN AND PENNER?
>> I JUST HAD A GOOD
CONVERSATION WITH SKUPIN, AND I
JUST SAID, "LOOK, IF I DO THIS
WITH YOU, YOU HAVE TO PROMISE ME
THAT PENNER WILL NOT STAY HERE
LONGER THAN US."
AND HE GAVE ME HIS WORD HE WOULD
VOTE WITH US TO GET PENNER OUT.
THE ONLY THING I CAN SAY IS HOW
MUCH-- I MEAN WE BUILT SOME KIND
OF VALUE WITH PENNER.
>> YEAH.
>> IF YOU AND I JUMP AND GO OVER
TO THE YELLOW TRIBE, YOU AND I
JUST MAY BE ON THE BOTTOM.
>> HERE COMES PENNER BEHIND US.
>> WHAT'S UP, PENNER?
>> HOW WE DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> WE'RE JUST TALKING THROUGH
ALL THE B.S. WE HAVE BEEN
HEARING.
>> WELL, LISTEN, YOU KNOW WHERE
I STAND.
AND I'M TOTALLY WITH YOU GUYS.
I HOPE THE HELL YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO VOTE WITH THEM AGAINST ME
TONIGHT.
YOU HAVE MY LOYALTY.
>> IF THE PEOPLE THEY BELIEVE
ARE GOING TO VOTE WITH ME ARE
REALLY NOT GOING TO VOTE WITH
ME, IF ALL OF THIS HAS BEEN
SMOKE, THEN I'M A TERRIBLE JUDGE
OF CHARACTER.
AND THEN I DON'T REALLY DESERVE
TO STAY IN THE GAME.
BUT I DO BELIEVE THAT SKUPIN AND
R.C. AND DENISE AND CARTER AND
JEFF, THEY'RE GOING TO VOTE WITH
ME.
THEY ALL MEAN IT.
I REALLY BELIEVE THEY DO.
LOOK, I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN TONIGHT.
BUT IF THERE'S A WAY THAT WE CAN
FLIP THIS VOTE, AND WE ARE THE
LAST PEOPLE STANDING THE FOUR
TIGHT KALABAW PEOPLE AND THE TWO
PEOPLE WE BROUGHT, IN WE CAN
TAKE CONTROL.
YOU KNOW?
THAT'S HOW I SEE IT.
WE'RE GOOD, OKAY.
WE REALLY ARE GOOD.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
WE'RE STILL HANGING.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DOING IT?
>> WE'RE STILL HANGING.
YEAH.
WE WANT THESE VETERANS OUT OF
HERE.
>> I'M NERVOUS HERE.
>> WE'RE ALL NERVOUS HERE ON
THIS THING.
RIGHT NOW, I'M ON A CROSSROADS.
I'M EITHER GOING WITH VETERAN
PLAYERS THAT I DON'T WANT TO WIN
THIS GAME AND RIDE THEM OUT, OR
I'M GOING TO GO WITH THE TANDANG
TRIBE AND GET PEN ERP OUT OF
HERE, BUT THEN I'M ON THE
BOTTOM.
IF YOU TREAT BASEBALL WITH
DISRESPECT, YOU'LL BE BIT IN THE
ASS, AND I KNOW YOU TREAT THIS
GAME WITH DISRESPECT, YOU'LL GET
BIT IN THE ASS TOO.
WITH ALL HUMBLENESS, I SAY THE
DECISION OF WHO GOES HOME
TONIGHT IS GOING TO BE HEAVILY
BASED ON WHICH WAY I GO AND WHO
I CARRY OVER TO THE OTHER SIDE.
I'VE GOT TO MAKE SURE I PROTECT
MYSELF BECAUSE WHATEVER MOVE I
MAKE, IT'S NOT GOING TO SIT WELL
WITH EITHER TRIBE.
>> Jeff: FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
DON'T HAVE A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB ONE, APPROACH
THE FLAME, DIP IT IN AND GET
FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO
SOMEBODY TONIGHT.
SO, WE'RE MAKING HISTORY.
THE ORIGINAL TANDANG SIX NEVER
LOST.
AND IN 25 SEASONS WE HAVE NEVER
HAD A TRIBE NOT GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL UNTIL THEY REACHED THE
MERGE.
ON THE FLIP SIDE, DENISE, YOU'VE
BEEN TO EVERY SINGLE TRIBAL
COUNCIL SINCE THE GAME STARTED.
>> EVERY ONE.
>> Jeff: AND WHAT'S AMAZING IS
YOU'VE SURVIVED.
>> I SOMEHOW SURVIVED IT ONE
MORE TIME.
I'M SAFE.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, 19 DAYS IN
THERE HAS TO BE SOME ANIMOSITY
WITHIN TANDANG.
>> TRUE.
LITTLE FRACT STARTED TO OCCUR
BUT IT'S KIND OF NATURAL TO
HAPPEN WHEN SIX OR SEVEN PEOPLE
GET TOGETHER.
YET, WE STILL PULLED OUT
VICTORIES.
>> Jeff: R.C., HOW BAD HAS IT
GOTTEN AT CAMP?
>> IT WAS PRETTY BAD AT TANDANG.
BUT WE'RE A FAMILY.
FAMILIES FIGHT SOMETIMES.
>> Jeff: ABI, THERE'S ONLY ONE
WINNER.
FAMILIES DON'T WIN SURVIVE.
>> RIGHT.
AND THE GAME HAS BEEN SHIFTING
CONSTANTLY.
I WAS VERY CLOSE TO R.C. IN THE
BEGINNING.
HOWEVER, SHE BETRAYED ME.
SO I HAD TO MOVE ON TO A
DIFFERENT ALLIANCE.
>> I AM GLAD THIS FINALLY CAME
UP BECAUSE I'M STILL UNAWARE OF
HOW I BETRAYED HER.
>> Jeff: WHAT HAPPENED, ABI?
>> WE FOUND THE CLUE FOR THE
IMMUNITY IDOL TOGETHER, AND HID
THE CLUE TOGETHER.
HOWEVER, SHE UNBURIED THE CLUE
WITHOUT TELLING ME, SO I CAN'T
TRUST HER.
>> I DIDN'T UNBURY ANYTHING.
I DIDN'T TOUCH ANYTHING.
>> I MEAN, IT WASN'T ME.
>> IT WASN'T ME.
>> AND THOUGHT IT WAS YOU.
BUT YOU BLEW UP AND WOULDN'T
HAVE A DISCUSSION WITH ME.
>> I TRUST MY ACTIONS, NOT YOURS
>> Jeff: SO, LISA, WHEN YOU
HEAR TWO TRIBE MATES FROM THE
ORIGINAL TANDANG SIX ARGUING,
CONCERN YOU AT ALL THAT SOMEBODY
FROM KALABAW MIGHT COME OVER AND
SAY, "LETCH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEM
IS.
COME OVER HERE AND WE HAVE FIVE
AND WE CONTROL THIS GAME."
>> IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT THE
WHOLE 11 PEOPLE, THEN THEY WERE
TOP DOG HERE STAYING WITH
TANDANG THAN GOING TO KALABAW.
AND THEN JUST GETTING VOTED OFF
AT THE END THERE.
>> Jeff: JEFF, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH LISA'S ARGUMENT?
>> THERE'S A TRIBE THAT COMES IN
WITH FOUR, AND IS OFFERING A
FIVE SLOT VERSUS A SIX OR A
SEVEN SLOT, THERE'S POTENTIAL
FOR A GAME--CHANGING SWITCH.
>> BUT ONCE YOU FLIP, YOU'RE NOT
REALLY A STRONG NUMBER.
YOU'RE A WEAKER NUMBER BECAUSE
YOU'VE SHOWN THAT YOU CAN'T BE
TRUSTED IN YOUR ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT
RETURNING PLAYERS.
TWO OF THEM ARE STILL IN THE
GAME, SKUPIN AND PENNER.
PETE, IS THERE A GROUP THOUGHT
IN TERMS OF YOU HAD YOUR SHOT?
GET OUT?
>> I MEAN, EVERY SEASON WHERE
THEY RETURN PLAYERS, USUALLY
PEOPLE DON'T LIKE THE IDEA THAT
THEY'RE HERE.
I MEAN, THEY'VE GOT TO PLAY THE
GAME BEFORE.
SO THERE'S ALWAYS A KIND OF
MUTINY FEELING.
BUT TANDANG HAS NEVER HAD TO GO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL SO YOU NEVER
REALLY KNOW WHAT WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED.
>> Jeff: IT'S ALSO ANOTHER
EXAMPLE WHY KALABAW IS LICKING
THEIR CHOPS.
R.C. COULD BE UP FOR GRAPS.
YOU SKUPIN COULD BE UP FOR
GRABS.
AND LISA IS THERE ANY CONCERN
MALCOLM AND DENISE STARTED THE
GAME TOGETHER.
THEY'RE BOTH STILL HERE AND NOW
THEY'RE BACK TOGETHER?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S A HUGE CONCERN AND IT
BRICKS UP SOMETHING YOU HAVEN'T
ADDRESSED.
THERE'S ALSO EVERY POSSIBILITY
THAT SOMEONE WHO IS ON THE
BOTTOM FLOOR IS THINKING IF I
COME OVER TO TANDANG, MAYBE I
CAN STAY A LITTLE LONGER.
I WON'T BE TOP DOG BUT AT LEAST
I WON'T BE THE DOG KICKED TO THE
SIDE OF THE ROAD SO THERE IS
ALSO THAT POSSIBILITY THAT COULD
BE HAPPENING.
>> Jeff: SO, PETE, WHAT'S THE
CONSENSUS ON THE IDOLS?
HOW MANY MIGHT THERE BE IN PLAY
TONIGHT?
>> I THINK THERE WERE TWO IN THE
GAME RIGHT NOW.
I'M PRETTY SURE MASTING'S IS
GONE.
>> Jeff: PETE, CONCERNED IT
COULD BE YOU TONIGHT?
CLEARLY, ARE YOU ONE OF THE FIT,
YOUNG GUYS WHO COULD DO WELL IN
CHALLENGES?
>> RIGHT, I FEEL I HAVE A HUGE
TARGET ON MY BACK.
>> Jeff: ABI, IS THAT
JUSTIFIED FOR PETE TO BE
CONCERNED?
>> ABSOLUTELY, YEAH.
>> Jeff: YEF JEFF, HOW LIKELY
IS IT THAT THERE WILL BE A
BLINDSIDE TONIGHT?
>> VERY LIKELY.
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING TO US FAIR
WHILE NOW.
YOU GET THE FACT WE'RE ALL
SCRAMBLING STILL AS WE SIT HERE
NOT KNOWING EXACTLY WHO'S GOING
HOME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELL,
CLEARLY, THERE IS A LOT OF
UNCERTAINTY ABOUT WHAT IS GOING
TO HAPPEN.
LET'S TRY TO BRING SOME CLARITY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ABI, YOU'RE UP
>> I NEVER LIKED YOU.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO
>> I'LL DO IT.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST PENNER
WILL NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, PENNER.
DOES NOT COUNT.
JONATHAN PENNER.
PENNER.
THREE VOTES PENNER, NONE OF THEM
COUNT.
R.C.
THAT'S ONE VOTE R.C.
PETE.
ONE VOTE PETE.
JOHN.
PENNER.
DOES NOT COUNT.
PENNER, DOES NOT COUNT.
R.C.
TWO VOTES R.C.
PETE.
TWO VOTES PETE.
R.C.
THREE VOTES R.C.
TWO VOTES PETE.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY, R.C.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
R.C., THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> BYE.
>> Jeff: WELL, BASED ON
EVERYTHING I HEARD TONIGHT, AND
WITH THREE PEOPLE GETTING VOTES,
IT WOULD APPEAR IT IS ANYBODY'S
GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": AFTER BEING
BETRAYED, PENNER'S GOT NOTHING
LEFT TO LOSE.
>> I HAVE NO ALLIANCES.
THEY ARE ALL READY TO DIE.
>> Jeff: HE WAGES WAR ON
EVERYONE.
>> MAYBE HE'LL WIN IMMUNITY NO
YOU WON'T, BECAUSE I'M WINNING
IMMUNITY.
I'LL STICK IT RIGHT IN THEIR
DAMN SPACES.
>> Jeff: ONE MORE SPOT!
>> THAT'S THE NAME OF THE GAME.
THE NAME OF THE GAME IS
BLINDSIDE.
IT WAS SUCH AN AMAZING,
WONDERFUL EXPERIENCE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I ACTUALLY GOT
TO DO THIS.
I LASTED RAIN AND NO FOOD AND
ALL THESE THINGS.
IT WAS DEFINITELY, BUT I GOT TO
PLAY "SURVIVOR."
HOW MANY PEOPLE GET TO DO THIS
AND I MADE IT PRETTY FAR SO I'M
VERY PROUD OF MYSELF.