>> jeff: Previously on
"survivor": After being bullied
Gullible.
>> jeff: Lisa jumped ship.
>> I can't be in an alliance
with someone who doesn't trust
Me.
>> jeff: Leaving pete and
Abipowerless.
>> I went from the top of the
pecking order all the way to the
Bottom.
>> who do you trust more, penner
or almalcolm?
Or almalcolm?
>> penner.
>> it's too easy for me to say
who I would go to the final four
With.
>> this is my final four.
>> penner didn't want to make
that kind of deal.
That kind of deal.
I think he missed an opportunity
gl at the immunity challenge--
Gl at the immunity challenge--
this is going to be very close!
This is going to be very close!
Carter is through!
Carter wins immunity!
Carter won.
Putting pete and abi on the
chopping block.
Chopping block.
But at tribal council, it was
only abi who took a beating.
Only abi who took a beating.
>> I have spent much of my life
with many people who are helpful
With many people who are helpful
and they're kind and there are
And they're kind and there are
many of these qualities that are
Many of these qualities that are
just not a part of who abi is.
Just not a part of who abi is.
>> I have never had that much
hatred towards me, ever.
Hatred towards me, ever.
>> jeff: And it only got worse
for abi when she played her idol
For abi when she played her idol
and watched her closest ally
And watched her closest ally
walk from the game.
Walk from the game.
Pete, the tribe has spoken.
Well, abi, your back supagainst
the wall, but anything can
Happen.
Seven are left, who will be
voted out tonight?
>> yesterday, you guys were
brutal towards me.
Brutal towards me.
I never felt that any of you
felt that way about me.
Felt that way about me.
It wasn't cute.
You understand that?
All right.
Thank you.
>> abi was sitting by the fire
with michael and as we're
With michael and as we're
overhearing it, it's just more
Overhearing it, it's just more
of the same.
Of the same.
She just continues the rein of
negative, grumpy abi.
Negative, grumpy abi.
>> are you hearing any of this?
>> I'm hearing all of it.
I just lay there and listen to
it all.
It all.
>> I just heard pieces.
>> it's just-- she's defensive,
Bitter.
>> between michael and malcolm
and lisa and I, we have our
And lisa and I, we have our
solid four.
Solid four.
Abi is the one going next,
unless she miraculously wins
Unless she miraculously wins
immunity, which I doubt, I
Immunity, which I doubt, I
highly doubt it.
Highly doubt it.
But if she does somehow have
immunity, jonathan's made it
Immunity, jonathan's made it
this far.
This far.
He's a great player.
Our next would probably be we'd
vote out jonathan.
>> there's a letter.
>> oh, my god, I'm going to
start crying again.
Start crying again.
>> come on, darling.
I wanted to give you a hug last
Night.
All right, come here
last nights kind of like the
Last nights kind of like the
tribe laid abi down in the
Tribe laid abi down in the
middle of the road, ran over her
Middle of the road, ran over her
with the bus and backed up and
With the bus and backed up and
do it over again.
Do it over again.
She just got destroyed.
>> denise--
>> denise was rough.
>> she said she would not want
to spend the rest of her days
To spend the rest of her days
here with me because I'm-- I'm
Here with me because I'm-- I'm
not a person she wants to relate
Not a person she wants to relate
with.
With.
>> I'm sorry, darling.
>> it was just eof, like-- it
was horrible.
Was horrible.
It was, like, the worst day of
my life.
My life.
>> abi's very unself-aware.
It's hard not to feel a little
sympathy for her when she's
Sympathy for her when she's
breaking down.
Breaking down.
So my heart goes out to her a
little bit.
Little bit.
>> let's see, let's see!
Ya!
Oh, I know what it is!
Food auction.
>> oh!
>> whooo!
>> oh, my god!
>> what have we got?
What have we got "going once,
going twice.
Going twice.
Some food today would be nice.
If you don't hurry and place
your bet, you may look back
Your bet, you may look back
hungry and wish you did."
Hungry and wish you did."
>> ya.
How fun.
>> I am the most unliked person
at this island right now.
At this island right now.
I'm going to have to just turn
my head around and move forward,
My head around and move forward,
and keep on playing the game.
And keep on playing the game.
Today's auction, I'm just going
to sit tight and hold my money,
To sit tight and hold my money,
and just wait for the right
And just wait for the right
opportunity to use my money
Opportunity to use my money
towards getting ahead, and
Towards getting ahead, and
they're not going to stop me
They're not going to stop me
now, no.
Now, no.
I'm better than that.
I'm going to fight.
I'm a fighter.
I'm a survivor.
>> jeff: Come on in, guys!
A lot of smiles for the
"survivor" auction.
This morning in tree mail, you
were each given $500 u.S.
Were each given $500 u.S.
Bidding will be in $20
Increments.
You cannot share food or money.
If you see something you like,
bid on it.
Bid on it.
The auction will end without
Warning.
Should we get started.
>> yes.
>> sure.
>> jeff: Pancakes, bacon,
butter, maple syrup, orange
Juice.
>> 200.
>> jeff: Wow, denise jumps it
right to 200.
Right to 200.
>> 320.
>> 500.
>> jeff: Denise just spent all
of her money.
Of her money.
>> I want it.
There's meat, there's some
Carbs.
I want it.
>> jeff: Sold to denise.
All the money she has.
>> she knew she wanted it.
>> that's $1.99 at the local
Diner.
>> perfect.
>> jeff: Well spent.
>> well spent.
>> jeff: Enjoy.
>> oh, my god.
>> jeff: Ready for the next
item?
Item?
>> 500.
>> he's an animal.
>> no chances.
I can't take a chance.
I'm thrilled to give you $500
for that.
For that.
>> jeff: Come on up, skupin.
>> oh, my gosh.
>> you're going to drink that
Wine?
>> I don't know.
I am not a drinker.
>> excuse me?
>> jeff: So that wine is just
going to go to waste?
Going to go to waste?
Because otherwise, I'll drink
it.
It.
>> no sir.
>> jeff: Take the food, have a
seat, enjoy.
Seat, enjoy.
Next item.
>> 20.
>> jeff: Iced coffee and
Donut.
20 to malcolm.
>> 80.
>> 200.
>> jeff: 200 to malcolm.
Going once, going twice.
Sold to malcolm for $200.
>> thatta boy.
>> that does look good.
>> oooh!
>> not bad, 200 bucks.
>> jeff: Enjoy.
Next item, this one will remain
covered.
Covered.
Blind bid.
>> I'll bid 100.
>> jeff: 100 to penner.
No activity from lisa and abi.
>> I know I'm going hom next so
I'm going to be eating soon.
>> so you're just going to keep
that money?
That money?
>> yeah, I'll keep the money.
>> jeff: $100 to penner is the
bid.
Bid.
Going once, going twice.
Sold.
>> well done, penner?
>> jeff: How do you know what
it is?
It is?
>> I think he got a steal.
>> jeff: This is the least
anybody has paid farn item.
Anybody has paid farn item.
>> oh,.
My.
God.
>> jeff: Pried chicken.
Even I can say from here that
looks pretty damn good.
Looks pretty damn good.
>> it's ridiculous.
>> jeff: You've got a weird
look in your eye.
Look in your eye.
You went somewhere else when you
took a bite.
Took a bite.
>>im somewhere else.
>> jeff: Enjoy.
>> well played, john.
>> gosh.
These smells around me right
Now.
>> jeff: Next item.
Will wemain covered.
>> 80.
>> 100.
>> jeff: $1 ha 100 to malcolm.
>> 120.
>> jeff: 180.
>> jeff: 180 to malcolm.
>> 200.
>> jeff: 200.
Going once, going twice, sold to
Carter.
>> thank you.
This is what you bought.
Now, before you dip in to this
beautiful baked potato, let me
Beautiful baked potato, let me
offer you a choice.
Offer you a choice.
You can keep this baked potato
or you can give up this baked
Or you can give up this baked
potato and trade it for the
Potato and trade it for the
tribe, right and beans.
Tribe, right and beans.
>> jeff: Should be plenty to
get you through the rest of this
Get you through the rest of this
game.
Game.
>> yeah!
>> ya!
>> jeff: Done.
>> carter's the man!
>> carter!
>> thank you!
>> you are a living legend.
>> jeff: Next item, covered.
>> 40.
>> jeff: 40 to carter.
And lisa in for the first time
at 60.
At 60.
>> there you go, lise.
>> 80.
>> 200.
>> jeff: Wow, she just jumped
Up.
>> 220, 260, 280.
>> 320.
>> jeff: $320 going once,
going twice, sold to lisa.
Going twice, sold to lisa.
Come on.
>> thank you, thank you.
>> jeff: $320.
I hope you like it.
>> ohio.
My.
God.
>> it's what you want uponned!
>> jeff: A nice gigantic
Sandwich.
Do you want to take a bite.
>> yeah.
Mmm.
>> amazing.
>> jeff: Next item.
This is an advantage in this
Game.
>> 500.
>> jeff: Just like that, abi
says 500.
Says 500.
That's what you were holding
your money for.
Your money for.
Sold to abi for $500.
Hold on to this.
>> I will.
>> jeff: When you get back to
camp, if you want to read it go
Camp, if you want to read it go
for it.
For it.
>> I will, thank you.
>> good for you.
>> jeff: Abi just spent all of
her money, the second you heard
Her money, the second you heard
advantage-- 500-- speaks to
Advantage-- 500-- speaks to
where you are at in game.
Where you are at in game.
>> absolutely.
There is no compassion towards
me here.
Me here.
I have to have compassion
towards myself.
Towards myself.
>> jeff: Next item.
>> 140.
>> 160.
>> 180.
>> jeff: 180 to lisa.
>> 200.
>> I don't have anything else.
>> jeff: 200 to carter.
Going once, going twice, sold to
Carter.
>> that isa boy.
Here's what your $200 bought
you, and it comes with a bit of
You, and it comes with a bit of
a twist.
A twist.
Veal shanks.
>> wow!
>> there you go!
>> jeff: For the entire tribe.
>> wow.
With no utensils and a 60-second
Clock.
Why don't you take the first
Bite.
>> thank you, carter, again!
Carter rules!
>> jeff: Once again, carter is
good for the tribe.
Good for the tribe.
60 seconds starts now.
>> go, tear it, tear it.
>> so good.
>> jeff: Nicely done.
That's how we finish a
"survivor" auction right there.
Great fun.
>> oh!
>> beans and rice.
>> it melted in my mouth.
Whatever that thing was.
Oh, my gosh!
>> was that good?
>> yes.
>> we had just come back from
this high elation.
This high elation.
Everybody was happy.
And just as we were just sharing
in the joy of this experience.
In the joy of this experience.
>> so you want to talk?
>> sure, I'm-- I will listen.
I think you need to do some
Talking.
I need to do some listening.
>> what do I need to say?
>> I don't know.
I'm sorry, maybe.
>> penner and abi start on this
conversation which of course
Conversation which of course
just shuts all of us totally
Down.
>> what should I apologize for?
>> for destroying me at tribal
Council yesterday.
>> I don't think I destroyed
You.
>> I was demoralized.
I was pointed fingers at.
I was ganged up on.
I left there crying, genuinely
Crying.
I just wanted to hear how you
Felt.
>> well, okay.
In a game, if you are that
blunt, that honest, it can feel
Blunt, that honest, it can feel
off-putting.
Off-putting.
So you might have been
Friendlier.
That's all.
Now it's your turn.
>> I have nothing to say.
I just wanted to hear what you
had to say.
Had to say.
>> I'm sorry, but it is really
hard not to laugh at some of the
Hard not to laugh at some of the
things she says.
Things she says.
>> I'm sorry if I was a bit too
honest with some of you.
Honest with some of you.
>> there's a saying in the bible
that says, "don't throw your
That says, "don't throw your
pearls before swine."
Pearls before swine."
I'm not calling abi a pig, but
at some point if someone is not
At some point if someone is not
going to value your words, then
Going to value your words, then
you don't keep giving them to
You don't keep giving them to
that person.
That person.
>> you know what, penner?
Everything that happens every
second in my life is a learning
Experience.
So, yes, absolutely.
I'm going to look back and I
will have learned something from
Will have learned something from
it.
Absolutely.
>> great.
And I'm sorry that it was jur
turn to get-- to get slammed.
Turn to get-- to get slammed.
I honestly, honestly empathize
with you.
With you.
The more bitter, the more
obnoxious, the more toxic abi
Obnoxious, the more toxic abi
is, the better for me.
Is, the better for me.
Easier it is to say, "we have to
get rid of her, right?"
Get rid of her, right?"
the six of us will figure it out
The six of us will figure it out
from there.
From there.
Come on.
Give me a hug.
Give me a handshake at least.
>> I'll give you a hug.
>> thank you.
>> don't give me a pat on the
Back.
Don't pat me all right?
>> all right.
>> all right, we'll continue.
>> everything that everyone is
saying I'm taking with a grain
Saying I'm taking with a grain
of salt because, you know, I
Of salt because, you know, I
think people are starting to
Think people are starting to
kind of feel like they need to
Kind of feel like they need to
start communicating with me
Start communicating with me
somehow because they don't know
Somehow because they don't know
what kind of a tool that I have
What kind of a tool that I have
in my hand.
In my hand.
The tool being what I bought at
the auction today.
The auction today.
You know, they realize that I
have a note.
Have a note.
I have an advantage in the game.
>> I was going to say, it's
either going to be-- there's an
Either going to be-- there's an
idol here somewhere or it's an
Idol here somewhere or it's an
advantage at the next immunity
Challenge.
Is there any other scenario you
can think o of?
Can think o of?
>> I got an advantage in the
Game.
I don't know what that details
to be.
To be.
So I need to open my note and
read it.
Read it.
This note could possibly change
my game if I play my cards
My game if I play my cards
right, yeah
Right, yeah
"move directly to the final
round in this challenge.
Round in this challenge.
You have a one in three shot at
win winning the immunity."
Win winning the immunity."
very cool.
Very cool.
I can do whatever I want with
this note.
This note.
And I'm going to tell them
whatever I have to, to have them
Whatever I have to, to have them
work on my favor.
Work on my favor.
I'm just going to have to put a
little bit of fear in them and
Little bit of fear in them and
try to break their alliance.
Try to break their alliance.
With this power that I may have.
But I do have a lot better
chance than I had before.
Chance than I had before.
Absolutely.
This morning, I woke up, and I
woke up very ambitious.
Woke up very ambitious.
I woke up with feeling that I am
not going to go without
Fighting.
They were having a lot of
problems with me being such an
Problems with me being such an
honest person, blunt person.
Honest person, blunt person.
They asked for this.
Now it's time for me to lie.
I'm going to outplay them.
I will be creating a fantasy
fourth immunity idol.
Fourth immunity idol.
>> while we have two minutes
without her, I'm just hoping we
Without her, I'm just hoping we
can all continue to stay strong.
Can all continue to stay strong.
I'm not that--
>> there's no temptation.
>> I'm not interested in going
forward with her opinion.
Forward with her opinion.
>> so I've been trying to plant
some seeds.
Some seeds.
At least I'm going to go out, or
I stay in the game as a very
smart, hardworking fighter.
Smart, hardworking fighter.
A warrior, really
I have some tricks under my
sleeve and I'm going to be
Sleeve and I'm going to be
pulling it off, and I would like
Pulling it off, and I would like
to have someone with me, because
To have someone with me, because
I don't think I'm going home the
next tribal.
Next tribal.
>> no?
>> nope.
>> abi is a bit like having a
gifl who just doesn't get the
Gifl who just doesn't get the
message and won't leave even
Message and won't leave even
after you have broken up with
After you have broken up with
her-- she's bitter.
Her-- she's bitter.
She hasn't forgiven you.
You're not getting the benefits
of having a girlfriend around
Of having a girlfriend around
anymore.
Anymore.
It's the worst situation
Possible.
>> there's a fourth idol, baby,
and I have it.
And I have it.
>> you have it already?
>> what do you think I have been
doing all day long?
Doing all day long?
>> I don't know.
>> no.
I woke up in the morning I've
been scrambling.
Been scrambling.
You guys are going to have to
make some decisions at tribal
Make some decisions at tribal
tomorrow that are not going to
Tomorrow that are not going to
have to be me.
Have to be me.
I'm telling you
>> crazy.
You guys ready to get to today's
immunity challenge?
Immunity challenge?
>> yup.
>> jeff: First things first,
carter.
Carter.
Once again, immunity is back up
for grabs.
For grabs.
For today's challenge, you will
be attached to a rope which is
Be attached to a rope which is
threaded through a hitching
Rail.
The first five to get through
move on to the next round.
Move on to the next round.
Where, still atasmed to a rope,
you must make your way through a
You must make your way through a
series of bamboo poles.
Series of bamboo poles.
The first two to finish make it
to the final round where you
To the final round where you
must navigate a multi-level
Must navigate a multi-level
obstacle course.
Obstacle course.
The first person to finish wins
immunity, guarantees what,
Skupin.
>> one in six, baby.
>> jeff: One-in-six shot at
winning this game.
Winning this game.
Losers go to trooibl and
somebody will be voted out.
Somebody will be voted out.
There is also a twist.
At the beginning of each round,
I'm going to ask you a question,
if you answer incorrectly you
If you answer incorrectly you
will have 5% of your body wait
Will have 5% of your body wait
added to you that you must carry
Added to you that you must carry
through the course.
Through the course.
One more twist, at the auction,
abi bought an advantage in this
Game.
It's a note.
To the read it.
>> I know I can't use proaps as
a tool at all, to keep the game
A tool at all, to keep the game
fair but I need to carry on with
Fair but I need to carry on with
my fake idol.
My fake idol.
There are two messages in this
Note.
It's up to me to read the second
message in the note.
Message in the note.
The first part of it says move
directly to the final round in
This challenge.
You have a one-in-three shot at
winning immunity.
Winning immunity.
I'm going to tear it into little
tiny pieces because I don't want
Tiny pieces because I don't want
anyone to know what the second
Anyone to know what the second
part of the message is.
Part of the message is.
>> jeff: All right, you can
take a spot at the end, abi.
Take a spot at the end, abi.
>> all right, good luck, you
Guys.
>> jeff: Everybody else, pick
your spots, and we'll get
Started.
All right, question for this
round:  The philippines consists
Round:  The philippines consists
of how many islands?
Of how many islands?
A, about 50.
B, about 500.
Or c, more than 5,000.
Everybody reveal.
Penner, carter, malcolm, skupin,
all say c, more than 5,000.
All say c, more than 5,000.
You are all four right.
Lisa got it wrong.
Denise got it wrong.
Both get weights.
>> oh, man!
>> oh!
>> jeff: All right, let's head
to our starting spots
To our starting spots
all right, here we go.
All right, here we go.
First round, denise and lisa are
each carrying 5% of their body
Weight.
Everybody else is clean.
First five finish move on to the
next round.
Next round.
Survivors ready?
Go.
Only one person will not survive
this round.
This round.
But for that person, it could
mean a million dollars.
Mean a million dollars.
>> lisa!
>> jeff: Lisa is doing a nice
job.
Job.
Malcolm right in there.
Carter struggling early.
Penner stuck at the beginning.
Really tied up.
Denise flying over this course.
Denise in the lead, skupin right
behind.
Behind.
There's malcolm.
Abi already guaranteed a spot in
the final.
The final.
Somebody could be in trouble
tonight from this tight group of
Tonight from this tight group of
six.
Six.
Denise has been on fire in this
Challenge.
She is not messing around.
Skupin and malcolm doing a great
job.
Job.
Carter has made a huge comeback.
Denise is through.
Moving on to the next round!
Skupe and I know malcolm very
close.
Close.
Carter made a huge comeback.
He's figured out how this
challenge works.
Challenge works.
From dead last to second place,
carter's moving on with denise.
Carter's moving on with denise.
>> whoo!
>> jeff: Skupin is moving on.
Malcolm moves on.
We have four people through.
We are looking for one more
person.
Person.
Lisa and penner.
Both have struggled in this
first stage.
First stage.
That extra bag of weight is
holding lisa down.
Holding lisa down.
Start move, lisa!
Let's go!
Penner through the last little
bit.
Bit.
Penner moving on.
It's denise, skupin, malcolm,
carter and penner moving on to
Carter and penner moving on to
the next round.
The next round.
All right, denise missed the
question in the first round and
Question in the first round and
the second round.
The second round.
Denise is now carrying 10% of
her body weight.
Her body weight.
Skupin and carter missed a
Question.
They are now each carrying 5% of
her body weight.
Her body weight.
Penner and malcolm are clean.
The first two to finish move on
to the final where they will
To the final where they will
meet abeerk going for immunity.
Meet abeerk going for immunity.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You're working your way through
these poles.
These poles.
There are a lot of them, and for
those of you carrying weight,
Those of you carrying weight,
that's another burden because
That's another burden because
it's sticking out somewhere.
It's sticking out somewhere.
You've got to squeeze through
these poles.
These poles.
It's tough enough without the
weight.
Weight.
Carter out to a bit of a lead.
Penner now making some ground
quickly.
Quickly.
>> I can't get through.
>> jeff: Skupe and I know
malcolm stuck.
Malcolm stuck.
Denise trying to get in it.
You're very close!
You've got to keep moving!
Carter near the end.
Penner near the end.
Two people are moving on.
Penner will be one with a huge
Effort.
Carter and denise are neck and
neck.
Neck.
Who will it be?
Cartir slides through.
It is cartir, penner, and abi in
the final round.
>> she can't win this.
She can't climb.
But watch how good her knee is.
>> jeff: Here we go.
We have abi who bought her way
into the final round.
Into the final round.
We have carter who is carrying
10% of his body weight after
answering another question
Answering another question
wrong, and we have penner who is
Completely clean.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
A little different this roind.
You have to make your way
through these little gates of
Rope.
You get there by untying knots
as fast as you can, and you
As fast as you can, and you
better be moving quickly.
Better be moving quickly.
Abi's through first.
Then carter.
Now penner in there.
Right off the bat, it is abi and
carter.
Carter.
Abi is clearly staithe she needs
It.
She spent $500 at the auction to
get the advantage, and right now
Get the advantage, and right now
it is proving worthwhile as she
It is proving worthwhile as she
is in the lead.
Is in the lead.
Abi is ahead of carter.
Penner right behind.
Abi is whipping through these
Knots.
Pulling away from carter.
>> oh, my god.
>> jeff: Penner now trying to
catch carter.
Catch carter.
It is abi's challenge to lose
Right now.
Could be the best $500 she spent
in her life.
In her life.
Abi heading to the second half
of this course.
Of this course.
Carter and penner trying to
catch it.
Catch it.
>> you're in, carter!
>> jeff: Abi continues to fly
through this course.
Through this course.
>> carter you're in it!
>> jeff: Indicator now gaining
on abi.
On abi.
>> go, carter, go!
>> jeff: He's got to pick it
Up!
>> come on, carter.
>> jeff: Pennener this.
>> abi has had the lead from the
beginning and she still has it.
Beginning and she still has it.
Carter trying to catch her.
>> go, carter.
>> jeff: Abi now at the last
gate of rope.
Gate of rope.
She gets through these knots,
abi will win immunity and be
Abi will win immunity and be
safe at tribal council.
Safe at tribal council.
Carter right there, trying to
get on it.
Get on it.
>> go!
>> jeff: Abi slides down.
Abi wins immunity.
>> yes!
Thank you, god!
>> jeff: Is safe at tonight's
tribal council and guaranteed a
Tribal council and guaranteed a
one-in-six shot at winning this
Game.
>> yes!
>> jeff: What a victory.
Abi, come on over.
What a journey it has been.
You went from being on top, to
being on the bottom, to being an
Being on the bottom, to being an
outcast to being safe.
Outcast to being safe.
Abi cannot be voted out tonight.
And that means, one of the other
six of you will be going home
Tonight.
Grab your stuff.
See you tonight at tribal
council.
Council.
Congrats.
Abi won immunity today.
She paid $500 for advantage and
it paid off.
It paid off.
She got to skip two-thirds of
the challenge.
The challenge.
I had to act upset.
Oh, no, this is horrible.
It's the worst thing in the
World.
I couldn't ask for a more
convenient excuse to get rid of
Convenient excuse to get rid of
a real threat in this game,
A real threat in this game,
which is penner.
Which is penner.
>> so everything's fine.
We're all writing down penner.
>> there's nothing he can do.
>> you know what, I think I have
surinized it.
Surinized it.
I love this game.
I'm just not cut out under this
game.
Game.
It's too big for me.
I'm in such this huge inner
Conflict.
I mean I like denise and
malcolm, but I really-- I really
Malcolm, but I really-- I really
have a heart connection with
Have a heart connection with
carter and penner.
Carter and penner.
And now I'm going to hurt
somebody I care about.
Somebody I care about.
I mean, it just is so hard.
>> I know.
And I know that's the hardest
part of this game for you.
Part of this game for you.
>> it is.
>> that's okay.
This is okay.
Because you know what?
Because we made a pact.
And we've stuck to it.
It's penner.
>> I love this game, and I want
to be a good player.
To be a good player.
I just-- I think perhaps I'm not
cut out for this game.
Cut out for this game.
I think it's too big for me.
I'm not very good at this game.
I just don't eye don't want to
lie to you that I'm totally in.
Lie to you that I'm totally in.
>> oh, come on.
Cut the crap.
Really?
Come on.
Let's go, you and I take a walk.
>> no.
>> you want to vote me out?
>> what do you want to do?
>> as a matter of fact, you
remember before we voted out
Remember before we voted out
peter, I came to you, and said,
Peter, I came to you, and said,
"I want to go to the end with
you and skupin?
You and skupin?
>> what's the problem?
>> you said, "I'd like that,
too, but let's see how this
Too, but let's see how this
shakes down, and get peter and
Shakes down, and get peter and
abi out of the way.
Abi out of the way.
It's a little too soon to be
talking that way."
Talking that way."
so you know that's what I
Wanted.
In the meantime, after that,
somebody came to me and said,
Somebody came to me and said,
you know, "want to be in an
You know, "want to be in an
alliance to the end?"
Alliance to the end?"
>> am I going home tonight?
>> not-- I mean, that's the name
I've been told to write down.
>> by who?
>> I can't tell you that.
I'm so not good at this game.
>> this is unbelievable.
This is unbelievable.
To me.
Because I didn't make empty
Promises?
After you had written my name
down twice?
Down twice?
And I appreciate that you-- I
Do.
I really appreciate what you're
going through, but not that it's
Going through, but not that it's
going to knock me out of the
Going to knock me out of the
game because I know you don't
Game because I know you don't
want to do that.
Want to do that.
>> I don't.
>> I know you don't.
>> I really, really-- I really,
really don't want to do that.
Really don't want to do that.
>> lisa once again lost her
Mind.
And she had to confess to me
that she was in another
That she was in another
alliance, that she's voting for
Alliance, that she's voting for
me tonight.
Me tonight.
And I guess to her credit she's
going to stick by her guns.
Going to stick by her guns.
She will not be suede.
I think her guns are ridiculous.
>> I to tell you, and I know you
believe me, I like you more than
Believe me, I like you more than
anybody out here.
Anybody out here.
I want to go to the final three
with you.
With you.
It's not about the money.
>> well, what are we going to
do?
Do?
What am I going to do?
>> I-- I-- I would say go do
your magic that you do.
Your magic that you do.
.>> okay.
Let the chips fall where they
may.
May.
Here we go.
Lisa got played.
And that's-- that is to denise
and malcolm's credit.
And malcolm's credit.
Now, my mistake, of course, was
I was playing both ends against
the middle without making a
The middle without making a
commitment to anybody.
Commitment to anybody.
That was probably my mistake.
I did not choose a side.
Well, we're going to vote for
Denise.
>> I'm on board.
People are a bit wary of malcolm
for his idol, and he's aligned
For his idol, and he's aligned
tightly with denise.
Tightly with denise.
So we will now vote for denise.
I'm going to check make sure
skupin is cool.
Skupin is cool.
>> all right.
>> carter, abi, and I are all
prepared to vote for denise.
Prepared to vote for denise.
And if you vote for denise,
that's that.
That's that.
I mean, unfortunately for you,
my brilliant, wise, old chum,
My brilliant, wise, old chum,
you put yourself in the driver's
You put yourself in the driver's
seat and you get to decide who
Seat and you get to decide who
you want to go forward with.
You want to go forward with.
I mean, that's just the way it
Is.
>> that proverbial swing vote.
>> you are now the swing vote.
>> will lisa change or is she
locked, based on what your
Locked, based on what your
perception is?
Perception is?
>> honestly, I could lie to you,
but I'd never lie to you.
But I'd never lie to you.
I haven't lied to you once.
She's right-- right now she's
conflicted but she does not want
Conflicted but she does not want
to go against her word.
To go against her word.
So she's going to vote for me.
And it's up to-- it's up to you.
>> tribal council day is a zoo.
My dilemma is I'm going to make
three people very happy tonight,
Three people very happy tonight,
and I'm going to upset three
People.
I'm going to potentially gain
three jury votes and lose three
Three jury votes and lose three
jury votes at the same time.
Jury votes at the same time.
>> buddy.
I'm langing-- I'm hanging on a
thread here.
Thread here.
Thank you.
>> so is the better group to win
the game with lease, denise, and
The game with lease, denise, and
malcolm, our abi, carter and
Malcolm, our abi, carter and
penner?
Penner?
And the closer it gets to the
final three, the more I realize
Final three, the more I realize
it's a pretty big deal.
It's a pretty big deal.
I believe strongly they could
beat pennener the final three
Beat pennener the final three
>> jeff: We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
The members of our jury.
R.C.
Jeff.
Artis.
And pete, voted out at the last
tribal council.
Tribal council.
Well, I think my final word at
the last tribal council were,
The last tribal council were,
abe it seems like your back is
Abe it seems like your back is
up against the wall, but
Up against the wall, but
anything can happen.
Anything can happen.
And what do you know?
It happened.
Here you sit with immunity.
Was that the plan going into the
auction, to wait for an
Advantage?
>> absolutely.
$500 is the best spent in my
Whole life.
>> jeff: Denise, last tribal
council was particularly brutal
Council was particularly brutal
for abi.
For abi.
You're a therapist.
What happens to people when
you're in these kinds of
You're in these kinds of
conditions that make you change
Conditions that make you change
how you behave?
How you behave?
>> I think what was perceived as
brutal was simply a group of
Brutal was simply a group of
people whose tolerance had just
People whose tolerance had just
reached their maximum.
Reached their maximum.
>> yeah.
>> jeff: So, penner, what was
the vibe back at camp today
The vibe back at camp today
after the challenge?
After the challenge?
>> well, it all got pretty crazy
in a way that I guess we all
In a way that I guess we all
hadn't anticipated.
Hadn't anticipated.
My sense was that abi was the
next to go.
Next to go.
But it seems like lines were
drawn that had been in the sand
Drawn that had been in the sand
all along.
All along.
I believe that denise and
malcolm shook hands and gave
Malcolm shook hands and gave
their words to skupin and lisa,
Their words to skupin and lisa,
as if that was the end-all, and
As if that was the end-all, and
be-all, when in fact you have
Be-all, when in fact you have
said I'm the person you trust
Said I'm the person you trust
the most out here.
The most out here.
I've given you guys nothing but
trust and loyalty.
Trust and loyalty.
>> but you didn't trust her
enough to make the alliance.
Enough to make the alliance.
>> right.
I did not trust her enough
because she voted for me twice.
Because she voted for me twice.
Took me a day or two or three to
think about it.
Think about it.
But I don't know, we've become
close over the last 12 days and
Close over the last 12 days and
had a lot of fun playing
Together.
So I'm appealing you to be my
genuine allie allies and give
Genuine allie allies and give
yourselves a real shot at the
Yourselves a real shot at the
million dollars, which I
Million dollars, which I
honestly don't you you have if
Honestly don't you you have if
you align with these two.
You align with these two.
That's the honest truth.
So I'm looking you in the eyes
saying please don't vote me out.
Saying please don't vote me out.
I want to work with you guys.
I've always only said that and
it's the truth.
It's the truth.
>> jeff: Malcolm, you're
shaking your head because he is
Shaking your head because he is
making the argument that would
Making the argument that would
turn the table on you and
Denise.
>> I don't want to get in an
argument with penner and brow
Argument with penner and brow
beat lisa.
Beat lisa.
We did have a bond.
He's not the only one in your
heart and I hope we're in your
Heart and I hope we're in your
heart, too, and I trust nut
Heart, too, and I trust nut
11th hour right now.
>> jeff: Lisa, this must be
very difficult for you.
Very difficult for you.
>> whatever I do is going to
hurt people they care about.
Hurt people they care about.
>about.
>> but if you do vote me out
tonight, you will give one
Tonight, you will give one
million to one were these two
Million to one were these two
people.
People.
>> thanks, buddy.
>> jeff: Pen eyou're argument
is not only does it help me
Is not only does it help me
because it keeps me in the game.
Because it keeps me in the game.
It helps you.
>> yes.
I mean, I honestly believe you
cannot with with win with them.
Cannot with with win with them.
I honestly believe that.
>> penner, that is absolutely
part of my consideration.
Part of my consideration.
>> fair enough.
Thank you.
>> jeff: Lisa, can you compare
this dilemma to any other
This dilemma to any other
situation in your life?
Situation in your life?
>> yes.
But it's too personal to talk
about.
About.
Yeah.
>> jeff: And how difficult was
that situation?
Huge.
>> jeff: So based on your
decision tonight, is there a
Decision tonight, is there a
chance you will disappoint
Chance you will disappoint
yourself?
Yourself?
>> yeah.
>> jeff: How tough is this for
you, skupin?
You, skupin?
>> you know, ge, I can't look at
any one of these people and say
Any one of these people and say
I would not like to be great
friends when this is over but
Friends when this is over but
I'd like to win, too, so I
believe there's some validity to
Believe there's some validity to
what penner said.
What penner said.
>> jeff: Well, the only person
who can truly feel safe tonight
Who can truly feel safe tonight
is abi.
Is abi.
Everybody else is fair game.
It is time to vote.
Denise, you're up
>> I hope guhome tonight.
Better.
>> denise.
>> jeff: I'll go tally the
votes.
Votes.
>> wonderful.
>> jeff: If anybody has a
hidden immunity idol and you
Hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
Want to play it, now would be
the time to do so
The time to do so
all right, once the votes are
All right, once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
Read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the tribal council area
Immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, denise.
Two votes denise.
Penner.
Jonathan.
Two votes denise, two votes
penner.
Penner.
Denise.
Three votes denise.
Penner.
We're tied.
Three votes denise, three votes
Penner.
One vote left.
12th person voted out and
the 55th member of our jury.
The 55th member of our jury.
Penner.
Bring me your torch.
>> bye.
Can I have a hug, too?
>> no, I'm not going to hug
anybody else.
Anybody else.
>> oh, okay
>> jeff: Penner, the tribe has
spoken.
Spoken.
Time for you to go.
>> that sucks, jeff.
Guys... Keep your sunny side up.
And suck eggs!
( whistling )
Is.
>> jeff: This game is clearly
up for grabs.
Up for grabs.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning brought to you by
survivor productions, cbs,
And ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
media access group at wgbh
Media access group at wgbh
access.Wgbh.Org
>> jeff: Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
>> jeff: Next time on
"survivor": A little bit of love
could go a long way.
Could go a long way.
>> I don't think I've ever
needed any person more in my
Needed any person more in my
life at this moment.
>> jeff: Or it could cost one
survivor everything.
Survivor everything.
>> he looks like a cornell.
>> my brother say knucklehead.
>> him running his mouth could
cost me.
>> my strategy, once again, has
failed.
Failed.
I'm very, very disappointed in
myself for not doing better.
Myself for not doing better.
But I guess that's the way
"survivor" crumbles.
I spent six years of my life
with "survivor."
With "survivor."
I'm one of the lucky few that's
played three times.
Played three times.
And it's been fun.
And extremely painful.