>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": IN THE BEGINNING OF
THE GAME, LISA WASAB OW CAST,
AND STRUGGLED TO HIDE HER
IDENTITY AS A FORMER TEEN STAR.
>> MAYBE I'M NOT ABLE TO PLAY
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: AS OF THE MERGE ONLY
TWO DISCOVERED HER SECRET,
PENNER AND SKUPIN, WHO HAD JUST
BECOME HER BIGGEST ALLY IN THE
GAME.
>> LISA IS IN THIS GAME TO WIN
IT, WHICH IS GREAT BECAUSE SHE'S
MY CLOSEST ALLY OUT HERE.
>> Jeff: LISA AND SKUPIN'S
ONLY PROBLEM WAS EVERYONE WANTED
A RETURNING PLAYER OUT NEXT.
>> I'LL JOIN ANY GANG AS LONG AS
I GET PENNER OUT BEFORE I GET
OUT.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE--
>> COME ON, JEFF, PEERPT.
>> Jeff: PENNER STARTING TO
PULL AWAY.
PENNURE DOWN TO TWO PIECES.
PENNER WINS IMMUNITY.
PENNER WON IMMUNITY AND LISA
DECIDED TO MAKE A BIG MOVE
ATTEMPTING TO SAVE SKUPIN.
>> MALCOLM HAS WANT IMMUNITY
IDOL.
>> Jeff: BY THROWING MALCOLM
AND HIS IDOL UNDER THE BUS.
>> EVERYBODY IS GOING MAD IN THE
PAST HOUR.
IF THIS THING EVEN SEEMSCROSE
I'M PLAYING IT.
>> .
>> I PUT MY FAITH IN A LITTLE
TEXAS GIRL AND SHE THROUGH ME
UNDER THE BUS.
>> I THINK THIS IS LUDICROUS.
AND MALCOLM WAS WAY SLONGENER
OUR ALLIANCE THAN SKUPIN EVER
WAS.
>> Jeff: AND IT BECAME CLEAR
THERE WERE TWO MAJOR ALLIANCES.
THERE IS THE TANDANG FIVE, AND
THEN THERE IS THEICAL BOW FOUR
AND MALCOLM, EACH WITH THEIR OWN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> THIS IS AWESOME.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, TANDANG
STAYED AND GOT THEIR WAY.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JEFF.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NINE ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS THE MOST
AMAZING EXPERIENCE BECAUSE LISA
MADE HER BIG MOVE TO SAVE ME.
SO GOING FROM "IT'S YOU" TO
"IT'S NOT YOU" IN THE MATTER OF
FIVE MINUTES IS A SENSE OF
RELIEF.
I MEAN, THE GAME COULD HAVE BEEN
FLIPPED AROUND WITH ONE OR TWO
MORE VOTES FOR PETE, BUT WHETHER
PETE WENT OR WHETHER JEFF WENT,
THEY'RE BOTH THE TWO MOST
OUTSPOKEN PEOPLE ABOUT GETTING
RID OF RETURNING PLAYERS.
SO HAVING ONE OF THEM GO WAS A
WIN-WIN FOR ME, EITHER WAY.
>> THANKS IF YOUR VOTE, MIKE.
THAT WAS LOVELY.
>> I DIDN'T VOTE FOR YOU, ABI.
I DIDN'T VOTE FOR YOU.
>> WHO VOTED FOR ME?
>>
>> DID.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> YOU VOTED FOR ME?
>> YEAH, I WAS P.O.'D.
SOME PLAN CAN THE B" GOING.
NOBODY TELLS ME ABOUT THE PLAN
"B."
THAT'S NOT VERY NICE.
>> YOU VOTED FOR ME?
>> I VOTE FOR YOU.
I DON'T LIKE BUYING PLAYED LIKE
THAT.
THAT PISSED ME OFF.
THAT WAS THE MOST INCREDIBLE
TRIBAL I HAVE EVER BEEN A PART
OF.
THAT WAS CRAZY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED.
>> SO WHO VOTED FOR JEFF?
>> ALL FIVE OF TANDANG.
>> AND MALCOLM AS WELL?
>> NO.
MALCOLM-- THERE WERE FOUR PETE,
ONE ABY, FIVE JEFF.
>> SO I AM THE ONE WHO BLEW IT?
BY NOT VOTING FOR PETE?
>> THAT SUCKS.
>> THERE WAS NO PLAN.
NOBODY KNEW WHAT WAS HELL WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
SO DID MY VOTE SCREW IT UP?
EVEN IF I VOTE FORWARD PETE,
TALL WOULD HAVE DONE WAS TIED IT
UP.
SO I VOTED FOR ABY.
AND NOW WE'LL SEE WHERE I STAND.
YOU KNOW, I'M A DEAD MAN WALKING
ANYWAY.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> NO.
>> IT WAS TERRIBLE.
>> YOU WERE PLAYING THE GAME.
I WAS PLAYING THE GAME.
I JUST WENT FOR IT.
>> THANK YOU, MALCOLM.
>> MALCOLM, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YOU UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> YOU KNOW, I TRIED TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE.
I TRIED TO PLAY THE GAME LIKE A
REAL "SURVIVOR," AND IT'S JUST
NOT ME.
AND I LIED, AND I BETRAYED, AND
I BROKE PROMISES.
MALCOLM, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
BEING SO FULL OF GRACE AND
MERCY, AND I AM SO GRATEFUL.
>> YOU WERE PLAYING THE GAME.
I WAS PLAYING THE GAME.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> YOU ARE JUST AMAZING.
>> IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I LOVE THIS GAME, BUT I THINK
IT'S TOO BIG FOR ME.
I DON'T THINK I'M-- IT'S BIGGER
THAN ME.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
♪ ♪
>> THERE ARE FIVE ORIGINAL
TANDANG STILL LEFT, AND IF THEY
VOTE TOGETHER, I'M DONE.
I'LL PROBABLY GO HOME AT THE
NEXT IMMUNITY, UNLESS I WIN IT.
BUT THERE HAVE BEEN SUCH
DIVISIONS, SO MANY CRACKS IN
THAT FIVE, AND THEIR IDENTITIES
AS PEOPLE IS SO VARIED.
YOU HAVE TWO PARENTS WHO ARE
TRYING TO PLAY A STRAIGHT-UP,
ALMOST CHRISTIAN GAME IN LISA
AND IN SKUPIN.
AND THEN YOU HAVE THREE
INCREDIBLY TIGHT PLAYERS WHO ARE
PLAYING SOME OTHER GAME, WHAT I
CALL A BULLY GAME.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> HOW AM I?
>> MY HOPE IS TO PLAY ON THOSE
DIVISIONS, TO APPEAL TO SKUPIN
AND LISA'S HEARTS.
WHY DID YOU THINK PEOPLE
WOULDN'T LIKE YOU THIS MORNING?
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T DO SOMETHING
THAT WAS PLEASING TO THEM?
YOU DIDN'T TRY TO PLEASE THEM?
>> BECAUSE I USED THEM AND
BETRAYED THEM.
>> DID YOU?
YOU EXPLAINED YOURSELF
BEAUTIFULLY LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS A BIG, BOLD SET OF MOVES.
MAYBE UNPRECEDENTED IN THE
HISTORY OF THE "SURVIVOR," BUT
YOU REALLY WERE TRYING TO WORK
FOR YOUR ALLIANCE, WEREN'T YOU?
OKAY.
WHO THE HELL CAN ARGUE WITH
THAT?
YOU KNOW.
I CERTAINLY ADMIRE YOU, LIKE
YOU, AND MAYBE EVEN COMING TO
LOVE YOU.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, THAT'S GOD'S
HONEST TRUTH.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT SOME OF THE--
YOUR HISTORY, AND YOUR CHILDHOOD
AND HOW THAT WOULD BE A VERY BIG
PART OF THE MAKEUP AND
PSYCHOLOGY OF SOMEONE WHO HAD
THE LIFE THAT YOU HAVE HAD,
BEING A PLEASER, BEING-- OF "AM
I OKAY?
DID YOU LIKE THAT?
WAS THAT GOOD?"
I KNOW EXACTLY HOW ONE LOOK FROM
THE WRONG PERSON SAYING, "YOU'RE
GOING TO GO OUT LOOKING LIKE
THAT?
YOU PUT ON A COUPLE OF POUND."
>> OH, MY GOSH, STOP.
YOU'RE KILLING ME.
>> A PERSON IN YOUR POSITION.
DEVASTATING.
AND SO HUTO BE A PLEASER.
I'M GONNA PAY FOR MY FAMILY'S
WHATEVER.
I'M THE BREAD WINNER.
I'VE GOT THESE RESPONSIBILITIES.
DO YOU LIKE ME?
AM I BEAUTIFUL ENOUGH?
AM I PRETTY ENOUGH?
AM I STAYING PRETTY?
AM I FUNNY ENOUGH?
I MEAN.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> THAT'S MY BUSINESS, TOO.
>> I KNOW THAT PENNER IS ALWAYS
SCRAMBLING TO FIND A WAY TO
STAY, BUT HE REALLY STRUCK
SOMETHING VERY, VERY DEEP, THIS
INTERNAL CONFLICT.
I THINK PROBABLY AT SOME LEVEL,
IT'S SPENDING A LIFETIME
PERFORMING, TAP DANCING, ACTING,
DOING WHATEVER IT TAKES TO DO
THE RIGHT THING, TO BE LIKED.
>> AND YOU ARE MAYBE ONLY NOW
REALLY GETTING TO DEAL WITH HOW
THE TOLL, THE COST OF THAT
EXTRAORDINARY YOUTH THAT YOU
HAD.
IT DID COST YOU SOMETHING.
YOU LOST SOMETHING.
AND NOW YOU KNOW.
AND I LOVE YOU.
>> MY WHOLE LIFE HAS BEEN BASED
ON PUBLIC PERCEPTION.
YOU BE, I'VE LIVED MY LIFE ON
THE SAME SINCE I WAS SEVEN YEARS
OLD.
AND EVEN BEFORE THEN, LEARNED TO
GET LOVE BY PERFORMING AND BEING
GOOD AND BEING LIKABLE.
SO THIS IS A WHOLE LIFETIME OF
THIS.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE YOU
CRY.
>> NO, IT'S-- JUST TO BE
UNDERSTOOD.
AND YOU HELP ME UNDERSTAND
MYSELF.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
IF I DO THE WRONG THING, WILL I
STILL BE OKAY?
IF I AM NOT LIKED OR IF I'M
JUDGED, WILL THAT BE OKAY?
CAN I SURVIVE NOT BEING, YOU
KNOW, LITTLE MISS PERFECT?
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>>
>> Jeff: FOR DADE'S CHALLENGE,
YOU WILL BE DIVIDED INTO TWO
TEAMS.
ON MY GO, ONE PERSON FROM EACH
TEAM WILL CRAWL THROUGH THE
MUDDY WATER, OVER THE A-FRAME,
AND INTO A PIT.
YOU'RE LOOKING FAIR BAG OF
BECAUSE.
YOU WILL THEN CRAWL THROUGH THE
RICE, PUT THE BAG ON THE TABLE,
THEN THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU HAVE COLLECTED ALL FOUR
BAGS, YOU WILL SHOOT THOSE BALLS
INTO THE BASKET.
FIRST TEAM TO GET ALL 12 BALLS
IN THEIR BASKET WINS REWARD.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TODAY'S REWARD SAY
NICE ONE BECAUSE THE WINNING
TEAM GETS TO GIVE AND RECEIVE.
THE WINNING TEAM WILL LEAVE HERE
AND BE TAKEN ON A LOCAL VILLAGE
WHERE YOU WILL BE "SURVIVOR"
AMBASSADORS.
>> OH!
>> COOL.
>> Jeff: YOU'LL BRING SOME
MUCH-NEEDED SCHOOL SUPPLIES AND
A LITTLE JOY IN THE FORM OF
TOYS.
>> THAT IS TOO COOL.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> Jeff: IN RETURN THE VILLAGE
IS COOKING FOR YOU A BEAUTIFUL
FEAST.
IT WILL BE A GREAT AFTERNOON AND
A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME EXPERIENCE.
WE'RE GOING TO CHOOSE OUR TEAMS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
OKAY, WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS FROM
THE SCHOOL YARD PICK WE HAVE
SKUPIN,AR TIS, LISA AND PETE.
AND WE HAVE PENNER, CARTER,
DENISE AND MALCOLM.
TWO TEAMS PICKED BY YOU GUYS.
THERE ARE NINE PEOPLE.
ONLY EIGHT ARE PLAYING.
ABY NOT PICKED.
ABY GOING TO SIT THIS ONE OUT
HAS NO SHOT AT AND REWARD.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
IT IS THE TWO RETURNEES LEADING
THEIR TEAMS.
PENNER AND SKUPIN.
THROUGH THE CRAWL.
NOW OVER THE A.
FRAME.
SKUPIN IS DOWN DOWN FIRST.
HEAD-FIRST INTO THE WATER.
PENNER RIGHT BEHIND.
NOW YOU'RE LOOKING FOR BAGS OF
BALLS. YOU'RE JUST LOOKING FOR
ONE BAG.
SKUPIN ALMOST LIKE HE KNEW RIGHT
WHERE IT WAS.
GRABS IT AND HE'S THROUGH THE
RICE.
PENNER STILL SEARCHING.
PENNER HAS A BAG OF BALLS
GO, YELLOW.
LISA NOW ON THE COURSE FOR THE
YELLOW TEAM.
PENNER IS LOOKING FOR ALL THE
BAGS FOR HIS TEAM AND PULLING
THEM UP.
>> I GOT THEM ALL, THEY'RE IN
THE CORNER.
>> Jeff: NEW STRATEGY BY THE
RED TEAM.
THAT COULD BE A BIG DIFFERENCE
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
LISA'S THREW OF THROUGH THE
CRAWL.
SHE'S COMING OVER.
GO, RED!
LISA DIGGING THROUGH THAT MUD.
IT WILL SUCK YOU IN.
>> THAT A BOY, CARTER.
>> Jeff: CARTER FLYING TRUE
THIS FACE-FIRST IN THE MUD.
>> THAT CORNER, RIGHT IN FRONT
OF YOU!
>> Jeff: PENNER HAS ALREADY
GRABBED THE BALLS AND PUT THEM
UP THERE.
EASY FOR CARTER.
LISA FIND HER BAG, BOTH ARE
THROUGH THE RICE.
CARTER HAS PUT THE RED TEAM IN
THE LEAD WITH THE HELP OF
PENNER.
GO, RED!
DENISE ON THE COURSE FOR THE RED
TEAM.
LISA STRUGGLING WITH THAT RICE.
>> COME ON, GET IT RIGHT HERE.
GET HERE, GET HERE!
>> Jeff: GO, YELLOW!
PETE OUT ON THE COURSE FOR THE
YELLOW.
DENEETS THROUGH THE CRAWL AND UP
ON THE A-FRAME.
DENISE WITH A HART HIT.
DENISE QUICKLY FINDS HER BAG.
AGAIN, THAT STRATEGY HELPFUL.
PETE IS OVER THE A-FRAME.
PETE NOW HAS TO DIG TO FIND A
BAG.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: GO, RED, GO!
RED WITH A BIG LEAD.
PENNER'S STRATEGY REALLY PAYING
OFF.
MALCOLM OUT ON THE COURSE IN THE
WATER.
ALL HE'S GOT TO DO IS PICK UP
THAT LAST BAG, AND JUST LIKE
THAT, MALCOLM HAS HIS FOURTH
BAG.
HE'S THROUGH THE RICE.
PETE STILL LOOKING FOR THE THIRD
BAG.
GO, RED TEAM!
PULL THE BALLS OUT OF THE BAG
AND START SHOOTING.
PETE HAS THE THIRD BAG FOR THE
YELLOW TEAM.
THEY ARE WAY BEHIND.
GO, YELLOW!
ARTIS THE FOURTH MEMBER FOR THE
YELLOW TEAM.
12 BALLS TOTAL NEED TO GO IN
THAT BASKET.
RED HAS ONE.
MALCOLM SCORESES ONE.
CARTER SCORES ONE.
ARTIS IS OVER THE A-FRAME.
HE'S STILL GOT TO FIND THE
FOURTH BAG.
RED TEAM HAS THREE BALLS NOW.
THIS COULD BE A BLOWOUT.
FOURTH BALL FOR THE RED TEAM.
FIFTH BALL FOR THE RED TEAM.
ARTIS FINALLY FINDS THE BAG AND
HE'S CRAWLING THROUGH THE RICE.
SLOWLY THROUGH THAT RICE.
SIX.
GO, YELLOW, TEAM!
START OPENING THOSE BAGS.
RED HAS SEVEN NOW.
MAKE THAT EIGHT.
THERE ARE ONLY 12 TOTAL.
MAKE IT NINE.
THREE BALLS LEFT FOR THE RED
TEAM.
12 LEFT UNDER THE YELLOW.
THAT'S 10.
PENNER SCORES ONE.
HERE COMES THE YELLOW.
A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE UP.
THAT'S 11.
ONE PLEFT FOR THE RED TEAM
YELLOW SCORES THEIR FIRST ONE.
MALCOLM FOR THE WIN.
SHORT.
IEL OW NOW HAS TWO.
MAKE IT THREE.
THEY'RE STARTING TO GET BACK IN
THIS.
MAKE IT FOUR FORIEL POPE RED
CANNOT GET THIS LAST ONE IN.
MALCOLM CAN DO IT.
NO.
MAKE IT FIVE FOR YELLOW.
RED LOOKING FOR THAT LAST POINT
AND A BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
THAT'S SIX FOR YELLOW.
THIS COULD DO IT.
MALCOLM WINS REWARD FOR THE RED
TAME TEAM!
PENNER, DENISE, MALCOLM, AND
CARTER WIN REWARD!
ALL RIGHT, PETE, SKUPIN, LISA,
ARTIS, AND ABI, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
CARTER, DENISE, MALCOLM, PENNER.
NICE JOB.
NICE REWARD.
ENJOY YOUR AFTERNOON.
>> HI!
HOW ARE YOU!
HI!
>> WE WALKED IN CARRYING THIS
BIG CRATE OF TOYS AND SCHOOL
SUPPLIES.
A GROUP OF UNBELIEVABLY CUTE
KIDS GRABBED OUR HANDS AND
WALKED US UP TO THIS LOVELY
NATIVE VILLAGE, WHICH IS
STRAIGHT OUT OF THE "BLUE
LAGOON" OR SOMETHING.
>> CHA IS YOUR NAME?
>> EDNA.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU, EDNA.
I'M DENISE.
>> MY NAME IS JONATHAN.
>> JONATHAN.
>> IN AMERICA MY NAME IS NORMAL.
>> NORMAL.
>> NO, NO, I MEAN IT'S--
( LAUGHTER )
THIS REWARD IS QUITE
EXTRAORDINARY.
PEOPLE OF ALL AGES ARE JUST
HANGING OUT TOGETHER.
BROTHERS, SISTERS, MOTHERS,
FATHERS, GRANDFATHERS, AND THEY
ARE WIDE OPEN TO THIS
EXPERIENCE.
READY?
AM I CLOSE?
WE PLAYED A LOCAL GAME WHICH IS
SIMILAR TO A PINATA KIND OF GAME
WE WOULD HAVE, AND I SORT OF,
YOU KNOW, JOKED AROUND A LITTLE
BIT, AND THE KIDS WENT WILD.
( CHEERS )
IT SEEMS TO BE THE HAPPIEST
COMMUNITY I'VE EVER WALKED INTO.
>> DO YOU HAVE BOYFRIENDS?
>> NO!
>> NO BOYFRIENDS?
>> WHAT ABOUT THEM?
>> NO!
>> RIGHT AIRFARE GRADUATED, I
TAUGHT ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN
MICRONESIA FOR A YEAR.
REMEMBERING ALL THE GOOD TIMES
I'VE HAD WAS A GOOD REMINDER OF
HOW MUCH I ENJOY WORKING WITH
KIDS, AND HOW FULFILLING THAT
CAN BE
( LAUGHTER )
>> WHAT!
WHY DID I GIVE THIS UP?
THIS MEANS SO MUCH FOR TO ME
THAN POURING DRINKS FOR GIRLS IN
BARS.
IT REALLY MADE ME CONSIDER WHAT
I WAS DOING WITH MY LIFE FOR THE
PAST YEAR.
IT REALLY WAS A LIFE-SHAPING
EXPERIENCE FOR ME.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I WANT SOME SO BAD.
>> YES, PLEASE!
I'LL HAVE EVERYTHING!
THE FOOD WAS FABULOUS.
>> NUM-NUM-NUM.
>> IT'S A GREAT BREAK FROM THE
GAME ALTHOUGH I HOPE WE GET TO
TALK STRATEGY OVER A BEER OR TWO
BECAUSE I'M IN A VERY TOUGH
POSITION.
>> THE ONLY THING THAT WOULD
MAKE THIS BETTER IS IF WE HAD
SKUPIN.
>> IF WE GET SKUPIN.
LISA I THINK WE HAVE TO BE
CAREFUL WITH.
>> SKUPIN WAS TREATED HORRIBLY
BY THOSE GUYS.
>> HE DIDN'T WANT TO LOOK LIKE A
TRAITOR.
>> THAT WOULD GIVE MORE MERIT TO
LEAVING THAT THAN STAYING WITH
THAT.
OUT OF JUST SOME SENSE OF
LOYALTY.
>> RIGHT NOW, THE LINES HAVE
BEEN DRAWN AND IT'S FORMER
TANDANG VERSUS EVERYONE ELSE,
BUT LAST NIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
THEY MADE A MOCKERY OF SKUPIN.
I FEEL LIKE HE'S BEEN MISTREATED
AND THEY MISTREATED LISA.
SO WE'RE TRYING TO GET SKUPIN
AND LISA IN WITH US BECAUSE
THEY'RE GOING TO PLAY THE
BIGGEST ROLE IN WHICH ALLIANCE
MOVES ON AND WHICH STARTS
GETTING PICKED OFF.
>> I'M PISSED, ARTIS.
>> ME, TOO.
>> LOSING A CHALLENGE LIKE THIS
IS AWFUL.
IT'S REALLY DEMORALIZING.
YOU KIND OF NEED THAT ENERGY.
BUT AT LEAST I GET TIME WITH
LISA WHO DOESN'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON AFTER THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL, WHERE SHE GOT
OBLITERATED, AND SKUPIN.
>> BUMMER!
>> YUP.
IT'S REALLY IRONIC SOMEONE I
WANTED TO GET RID OF FIRST OR
SECOND THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE
GAME NOW I'M FORCED TO WORK
WITH.
BUT WE NEED THE MAJORITY RIGHT
NOW, AND IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER WHO IT IS, BUT WHY NOT GO
TO THE PEOPLE THAT WE STARTED
THIS GAME WITH?
WE'RE BACK TO TANDANG STRONG.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRUST US A LOT
MORE THAN THEY'RE GOING TO TRUST
PENNER OR ANYBODY.
SO GETTING THEM CLOSE AND
KEEPING THEM CLOSE IS DEFINITELY
WHAT WE'RE TRYING TO DO, AND
MAKING THEM FEEL COMFORTABLE.
>> YOU KNOW, IF PENNER DOESN'T
WIN IMMUNITY NEXT, HE NEEDS TO
GO.
>> NO, I KNOW.
>> HE NEEDS TO GO ASAP.
HE'S VERY DANGEROUS.
>> AND HE'S ANNOYING.
>> YEAH, AND HOPEFULLY YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO BE... AGAIN, LISA.
YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO BRING
INFORMATION FROM OUR SIDE TO
THEM.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BRING THAT UP
AGAIN.
I'M JUST LETTING YOU KNOW.
>> I'D LIKE TO SAY, SOME MAY I
SAY SOMETHING--
>> ANYWAY, WITH ALL OF THAT
BEING SAID, I UNDERSTAND
EVERYTHING YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY.
I THINK YOU'RE JUST GULLIBLE.
I THINK YOU'RE JUST NAIVE, AND
YOU JUST DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO-- TO
DO BOTH.
YOU KNOW-- YOU-- YOU JUST DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> ABY IS JUST A LOOSE CANNON.
SHE THINKS SHE KNOWS SO MUCH
ABOUT THE GAME AND SO MUCH ABOUT
PEOPLE IN GENERAL.
I DON'T KNOW WHO TOLD HER THAT.
BUT SHE NEEDS TO SHUT UP BEFORE
SHE SCHIEWZ EVERYTHING ALL UP.
>> IT'S VERY IMPORTANT FOR US
FIVE RIGHT NOW, AND HOPEFULLY
MIKE WILL BE ON BOARD, TOO, TO
MAKE SURE THAT FTHAT MAN,
PENNER, DOES NOT WIN IMMUNITY
TOMORROW, HE'S GOING HOME.
ALL FIVE OF US HERE NEEDS TO
VOTE FOR HIM BECAUSE I'M SURE
THEY'RE GOING TO VOTE FOR ME OR
FOR PETER AGAIN.
SO WE HAVE TO BE REALLY STRONG,
THE FIVE OF US.
>> ONCE PENNER GOES HOME, THIS
IS A CAKEWALK.
>> YEAH, LIKE BEING-- YOU JUST
NEED TO BE A FIGHTER NOW AND YOU
HAVE TO MAKE SURE PENNER GOES
HOME.
>> I'M ALL FOR THAT.
VERYINTERESTING HOW THINGS SPLIT
AT THE CHALLENGE TODAY.
MY THOUGHT WAS AT LEAST WE GOT
SOME TIME.
MAYBE WE COULD REEVALUATE AND BE
SOLAND I HAD BE TANDANG FIVE.
BUT THEN I GET BACK HERE TO THE
ISLAND, AND ABI WAS TERRIBLE.
>> YOU GOTTA KEEP SKUPIN ON A
LITTLE BIT OF A LEASH, TOO--
>> OH, YEAH, DEFINITELY.
>> SO MAYBE IT MAKES SENSE TO GO
WITH THE OTHER ALLIANCE.
BUT I'VE MADE THIS GRAND STAND
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR LOYALTY TO
TANDANG TO KEEP SKUPIN, SO TO
FLIP OVER TO KALABAW LOOKS ON
THE OUTSIDE REALLY AWFUL, BUT ON
THE INSIDE, IT PROBABLY MAKES
MORE SENSE.
SO I'M JUST ABSOLUTELY-- I DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHAT TO THINK NOW.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> YUP.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
PENNER.
I HAVE TO TAKE IT BACK.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING TO HELP.
>> OH, NO.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
EACH BALANCE AN OVERSIZED PADDLE
ON A STAND.
YOU'LL ROLL A BALL DOWN THE
PADDLE AND ATTEMPT TO LAND IT IN
ONE OF SIX SPOTS.
FIRST PERSON TO GET A BALL ON
ALL SIX SPOTS WINS IMMUNITY IS
SAFE FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL,
GUARANTEED A ONE IN EIGHT SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
A LOT OF SMILES ON THAT.
GOOD ODDS, HUH, ART, A S?
>> REALLY GOOD ODDS IF YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
>> Jeff: LOSERS WILL GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
A ONE IN EIGHT SHOT AT WINNING
THIS GAME.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
OBVIOUSLY, THERE WILL BE A
LEARNING CURVE TO THIS.
YOUR GOAL IS TO LAND SIX BALLS
ON YOUR PADDLE ALL AT ONCE.
>> SORRY.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN LANDS HIS
FIRST WALL.
PETE LANDS ONE.
ARTIS CLOSE.
SKUPIN LANDS A SECOND WALL.
LISA'S GOT NOTHING.
ABI HAS NOTHING.
PENNER'S GOT NOTHING.
PETE LOOKING FOR THAT SECOND
BALL AND HE'S GOT IT.
PETE NOW WITH TWO.
SKUPIN WITH TWO.
SKUPIN WITH THREE NOW LOOKING
FOR HIS FOURTH.
SKUPIN WITH FOUR.
PETE LANDS HIS FOURTH.
PETE NOW WITH FOUR.
SKUPIN WITH FOUR.
A TWO-HORSE RACE RIGHT NOW.
IT'S GOING VERY QUICKLY THESE
GUYS.
SKUPIN CLOSE TO HIS FIFTH.
SKUPIN STICKS HIS FIFTH ONE.
PETE KNOCKS ONE OF HIS OFF.
NOW PETE'S GOT ANOTHER ONE
ROLLING.
PETE LOSING OAR ONE, DISASTER.
PETE LOSES TWO BALLS ON THAT
ONE.
SKUPIN LOOKING FOR HIS SIXTH AND
FINAL BALL TO WIN IMMUNITY.
AND HE DOES IT.
SKUPIN WINS IMMUNITY!
GUARANTEED A ONE IN EIGHT SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
>> NICE JOB!
WHAT THE HELL!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT IT'S GOING
TO TAKE TO WIN IMMUNITY ON THIS
SHOW.
SKUPIN SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> THERE YOU GO, SCUPPER.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY ELSE IS
FAIR GAME.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL,
NECESSARY SOMETHING GOES WRONG
WE CAN GET PENNER OUT AND WE CAN
ACTUALLY FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A
LONG TIME, COME BACK TO CAMP,
TAKE A DEEP BREATH AND SAY
WOOSAA.
>> A NEW CHALLENGE WIN-TIME
RECORD.
>> I DIDN'T WIN THAT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
SO I BE MY DAYS ARE NUMBERED IF
I CAN'T PUT SOMETHING TOGETHER.
THE PROBLEM IS THE NUMBERS.
I NEED FIVE VOTES TO EVEN HAVE
AN ICE CUBE'S CHANCE OF HELL OF
STAYING IN THE GAME.
>> I CAN'T BEAT YOU GUYS AT THE
PHYSICAL ONES.
I MIGHT AS WELL BEAT YOU AT THE
BALANCE ONES.
>> I WISH I WOULD BE VOTING OFF
MIKE TODAY, BUT WE NEED HIM FOR
THE NUMBERS.
>> YEAH, I WAS LOUSY AT THAT.
I GOT ONE.
>> PENNER IS A WIGGER THREAT,
THOUGH, BUT MIKE IS REALLY
ANNOYING.
>> IT'S SO DIFFERENT HAVING
IMMUNITY.
INDIVIDUAL, THAT IS.
OH!
>> SORRY.
SORRY, ARE YOU OKAY?
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I MEAN, I'M NOT GOING TO DIE.
>> YOU KNOW, PENNER IS ACTUALLY
REALLY CHARMING.
A LITTLE TOO SMART FOR HIS OWN
GOOD.
SO TIME FOR HIM TO GO HOME.
>> UNLESS ONE OF OUR TWO PEOPLE
THAT I AM CONCERNED ABOUT TURNS
ON US TONIGHT.
>> NAH.
>> BUT I DON'T KNOW.
LEASE AND SKUPIN KIND OF WORRY
ME.
>> SHHH.
>> HERE'S A THOUGHT-- AND I
DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS THINK--
I'M AFRAID, ONE, ABI COULD BE
SELFISH AND JUST PLAY THE IDOL
HERSELF.
SHE COULD END UP PASSING IT OFF
TO PETE.
>> HEY, GUYS!
I JUST FOUND A HUGE CLAM.
>> SHE FOUND A CLAM.
>> YA, WHOOPI.
YOU KNOW SHE'S NOT GOING TO GIVE
IT TO ARTIS.
ONE THOUGHT IS TO VOTE ARTIS.
>> ARTIS IS A SURE THING.
>> SHOULD I TELL PENNER ARTIS.
>> YOU KNOW, RIGHT NOW, I'VE GOT
MY ALLIANCE WITH MALCOLM AND THE
FORMER KALABAW TRIBE, CARTER AND
JONATHAN, AND THE GOAL FOR
TONIGHT IS DEFINITELY TO GET RID
OF ONE OF THE ORIGINAL TANDANG
MEMBERS, BREAK THAT LITTLE
EMPIRE UP, AND THEN REALLY
CONTINUE TO JUST TURN THIS GAME.
BUT THE PLAN VERY MUCH HINGES ON
SKUPIN AND LISA.
IF WE CAN'T GET THE NUMBERS,
JONATHAN IS GOING HOME.
>> I'M GOING TO ASK YOU A
QUESTION.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M LIKE A STORYTELLER.
THAT'S WHAT I DO, YOU KNOW?
"SURVIVOR" IS A BIG STORY.
WHAT'S THE STORY THAT'S GOING TO
BE TOLD THIS SEASON?
WHO ARE THE GOOD GUYS AND WHO
ARE THE BAD GUYS?
WHO IS THE UNDERDOG?
WHO IS THE AUDIENCE GOING TO BE
ROOTING FOR, CONSCIOUSLY OR NOT?
WHAT DOES THE AUDIENCE WANT TO
HAVE HAPPEN?
THE AUDIENCE IS GOING TO WATCH
YOU.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO SAY, "SHE'S
BEING LOYAL TO THE PEOPLE THAT
SHE'S BEEN LOYAL TO ALL ALONG,
AND THAT'S A WONDERFUL THING."
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT THEY ARE NOT GOING TO BE
HAPPY THAT YOU ARE HELPING THESE
THREE GUYS GO FURTHER, AND I'M
NOT GOING TO TRY TO INFLUENCE
YOU TO COME OVER TO MY SIDE, BUT
I HOPE THAT YOU AND SKUPIN DO
THE RIGHT THING AND TELL A
BETTER STORY.
>> I LIKE JONATHAN SO MUCH.
I'VE LEARNED SO MUCH FROM HIM
OUT HERE.
BUT, MAN, MY HEAD IS SPINNING.
I STILL WANT TO BE LOYAL.
BUT IS THAT THE OLD LISA?
IS THAT THE LEASE ON WHAT SPENT
HER LIFE WONDERING WHETHER BWHAT
OTHER PEOPLE ARE THINKING?
>> LISTEN, THIS IS MY
PERSPECTIVE ON THE STORY.
AND YOU'RE IN THE THICK OF IT.
YOU MIGHT BE THE FULCRUM
CHARACTER, YOU KNOW.
I AM PLANTING SEEDS WITH LISA
BECAUSE I'M PLAYING MY ASS OFF
OUT HERE.
BUT I CANNOT PANIC.
I HAVE TO BE CALM, COOL,
COLLECTED.
AND I HOPE THAT I GOT TRUE TO
HER, WHETHER IT CHANGES HER VOTE
OR NOT, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I ONLY NEED ONE OF THEM,
EITHER HER OR SKUPIN.
HOW DO YOU FEEL, HONESTLY?
DO YOU FEEL THAT YOU CAN VOTE
WITH US AND NOT WITH THEM?
WITH US?
WE'RE GUARANTEED THE FINAL FIVE.
YOU'RE THE FULCRUM VOTE.
I THINK THAT YOU COULD GO EITHER
WAY.
>> I KNOW THAT PEN SER
INTERESTED IN CREATING
SOMETHING.
>> LET'S LOCK IT DOWN.
IT'S ARTIS--
>> BUT LISA AND I AGREED ON DAY
ONE WE'LL ALWAYS TELL EACH OTHER
THE TRUTH, AND, YOU KNOW, SHE
ORCHESTRATED A PRETTY BIG MOVE
THE OTHER DAY IN AN EFFORT TO
SAVE THE TANDANG ALLIANCE IN
ORDER TO SAVE ME, SO I WANT TO
PLAY THIS GAME WITH LISA.
BUT I'VE GOT TO MAKE SURE IF I'M
GOING TO MAKE A BOLD MOVE THAT
SHE'S FIRMLY ON THE SIDE THAT
I'M CHOOSING.
>> WELL, TALK TO ME.
HELP ME OUT HERE AS FAR AS THE
BIG PICTURE HERE.
YOU UPON, THERE KNOW, THERE'S
THOUGHTS.
ONE, WHICH GROUP CAN YOU GET
FURTHER WITH?
TWO, WHICH GROUP WOULD YOU
RATHER PLAY WITH?
MY QUESTION IS ALWAYS THEN HOW
CAN WE STAY LOYAL TO SOMEBODY
WHO IS NOT LOYAL TO US.
>> RIGHT.
>> LIKE, WHERE IS THAT LOYALTY?
>> WHAT ABOUT BIGGER PICTURE,
YOU KNOW, IT LOOKS LIKE I'M
SWINGING HERE, SWING THERE,
LOYAL HERE, LOYAL THERE, SAYING
THIS AND CHANGING MY MIND.
THE BIGGER PICTURE.
>> THE BIGGER PICTURE SUAND I
HAVE AN ALLIANCE TO THE VERY
END.
SO, I MEAN, IS THERE EVEN THE
THOUGHT OF YOU GOING THE OTHER
WAY?
>> I'M REALLY CONSIDERING IT.
FROM THE BEGINNING I'VE THOUGHT
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS KEEP
TANDANG MEMBERS STRONG BECAUSE I
WANT TO STAY LOYAL TO TANDANG.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO SAY FROM
THE BEGINNING I WAS LOYAL TO
TANDANG.
BUT IF TANDANG IS NO LONGER
LOYAL TO ME, THEN AM I BEING
EXACTLY WHAT ABI ACCUSES ME OF
BEING-- JULLIBLE AND NAIVE?
AND I HAVE TO REALLY THINK ABOUT
THAT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
R.C.
AND JEFF VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS ONE OF
THE CRAZIEST I'VE EVER SEEN.
LISA, WAS THERE MUCH FALLOUT?
>> THE FALLOUT WAS SO INTERNAL
IN ME.
AND YET, WHEN I GOT BACK TO THE
ISLAND, I WAS WELCOMED WITH SUCH
GRACE.
EVERYBODY SAID, "IT'S A GAME.
YOU TRIED TO MAKE A BIG MOVE.
YOU DIDN'T PLAY IT TOO WELL, BUT
YOU WERE PLAYING IT."
>> Jeff: ABI, YOU WEREN'T
HAPPY AT ALL AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
DID YOU SHOW GRACE TO LEASE AS
WELL?
>> DID I SHOW GRACE TO YOU AS
>> I ACTUALLY EXPERIENCED MORE
DWRAIS FROM THE PEOPLE THAT I
WAS AGAINST THAN THE PEOPLE I
WAS TRYING TO PROTECT THE
NUMBERS FOR.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THAT
INDICATIVE OF, LISA?
>> MATURITY.
EXPERIENCE.
I THINK THERE ARE MORE
"SURVIVOR" FANS ON THE OTHER
ALLIANCE THAT COULD SEE I WAS
TRYING TO FLUSH OUT AN IDOL, AND
BLINDSIDE THE BIGGEST THREAT,
PROTECT SKUPIN AND KEEP THE
NUMBERS AND DO EVERYTHING, AND
THEN THE PROVERBIAL POOP HIT THE
FAN, AND THE FAN WAS POINTED
TOWARDS ME AND LANDED ON ME.
>> Jeff: ABI, I HAVE TO SAY
THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE IS SO
TENSE IT'S LIKE VENOM IS READY
TO COME OUT.
>> I WAS PAYING ATTENTION TO
WHAT SHE HAD TO SAY.
IT'S INTERESTING.
I MEAN, THAT THE OTHER ALLIANCE
IS MORE PROTECTIVE OF HER THAN
WE ARE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
>> Jeff: I.
>> Jeff: I DIDN'T HEAR HER SAY
PROTECTIVE.
I JUST HEARD HER SAY THEY SHOWED
GRACE.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
I FELT LIKE I HAD SHOWN GRACE TO
HER AS WELL, BUT APPARENTLY NOT.
>> Jeff: ARTIS, ARE YOU
SURPRISED THAT THIS DEEP INTO
THE GAME IT'S STILL TANDANG
VERSUS KALABAW?
>> NO.
TANDANG HAD ONE OF THE MOST
POWERFUL TRIBES PUT TOGETHER IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY AND IT'S
PLAYING OUT LIKE IT'S SUPPOSED
TO PLAY OUT.
>> Jeff: TENIECE?
>> THAT'S ONE WAY TO LOOK AT IT.
BUT BIG MOVES ARE ALWAYS MADE IN
THIS GAME AND WHO KNOWS WHEN
THINGS CAN SHIFT.
SO TO THINK IT CONTINUES TO GO
SMOOTHLY I THINK IT'S A REAL
RISK TO TAKE IN THIS GAME TO
THINK THAT WAY.
>> LET'S CLEAR THE AIR.
I'M NOT SAYING I'M TOTAL LEEL
100% COMFORTABLE AND SAFE.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND AT ANY
MOMENT IN THIS GAME I COULD BE
BLINDSIDED JUST LIKE ANYBODY
ELSE.
>> Jeff: SO, PENNER, WAS WITH
SKUPIN HAVING THE NECKLACE
TONIGHT DOES IT GO BEYOND
FEELING SAFE?
THAT IS CURRENCY AROUND HIS
NECK.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK A NUMBER OF US HAVE OVER
THE COURSE OF THE LAST NUMBER OF
DAYS SEEN OURSELVES AS MAYBE
FULCRUM VOTES, THAT THIS COULD
BE A WAY TO TIP THE BALANCE ONE
WAY OR THE OTHER, AND I GUESS
TONIGHT WE'LL FIND OUT.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, NOT ONLY DO
YOU HAVE IMMUNITY TONIGHT, YOU
HAVE A VOTE.
AND WITH NINE PEOPLE, WE'RE
GETTING DOWN TO IT.
>> I'LL TELL YOU, HAVING THIS
AROUND YOUR NECK IS AN
UNBELIEVABLE FEELING.
I NEVER FELT IT BEFORE.
IT'S BEEN 12 YEARS, AND I'VE
NEVER GIVEN UP THE DREAM OF
PLAYING THIS GAME AGAIN BECAUSE
I CAME OUT ORIGINALLY FOR THE
MONEY.
AND THEN THE GAME GOT BIGGER
THAN THE MONEY.
>> Jeff: SO AS A FAN OF THE
GAME, DID YOU APPRECIATE LISA'S
MOVE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL?
>> WELL, AND IT WAS REALLY FOR
THE WHOLE TANDANG TRIBE AT THAT
POINT.
THE I LOVED IT.
I LOVED THE MOVE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF?
ONE THING I HAVE LEARNED IS THAT
MY LIFE IS BIGGER THAN THIS
GAME, AND THIS GAME IS BIGGER
THAN ME.
>> Jeff: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> WHAT THAT MEANS IS, IS THIS
JUST A GAME OR CAN I JUST CUT
OFF MY HEART TO PLAY IT?
AND THEN I LEARN, NO, I CAN'T.
AND THIS IS SUCH A HUGE,
LIFE-ALTERING EXPERIENCE FOR ME
ALREADY, AND I DON'T KNOW IF I
CAN LEARN IT ALL IN 39 DAYS.
BUT I DO KNOW THESE 39 DAYS ARE
GOING TO PROBABLY CHANGE MY MORE
THAN MAYBE 39 OF MY 49 YEARS.
>> Jeff: PENNER, YOU'VE GOT TO
APPRECIATE SOMEBODY WHO PLAYS
THIS GAME.
>> I DO APPRECIATE IT.
AND I HOPE THAT THE NUMBERS MAY
HAVE SHIFTED, AND I'LL STAY IN
THE GAME.
THAT'S WHAT I'M HOPING FOR.
>> Jeff: DENISE, IS EVERYONE
AWARE THERE'S A CHANCE THE
NUMBERS COULD HAVE SHIFTED?
>> YOU KNOW, I HONESTLY DON'T
THINK THE TANDANG TRIBE BELIEVES
THE NUMBERS WILL SHIFT, BUT
DEFINITELY THAT'S THE HOPE.
THE NUMBERS MAY SHIFT AND THINGS
WILL BE UPSIDE DOWN TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: ABI, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GOING TO
HAPPEN TONIGHT?
>> I HOPE TANDANG HAS THE
NUMBERS, AND I DON'T AGREE WITH
YOU.
I THINK THAT TANDANG HAS REALLY
CONSIDERED THAT WE DO NOT HAVE
THE NUMBERS.
WILL BE.
>> Jeff: AND WHAT WOULD THAT
MEAN?
WHO WOULD YOU NOT HAVE?
>> I AM NOT VERY SURE ABOUT LISA
AT THIS POINT.
>> INCREDIBLE.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> JEFF, THIS IS WHAT I HAVE
GOTTEN ALL ALONG.
AND I'VE TRIED TO SAY THAT
ACTIONS SPEAK LOUDER THAN WORD,
AND MY ACTION HAVE ONLY BEEN
LOYAL TO TANDANG.
BUT, YOU KNOW, MAYBE I NEED TO
HEAR THESE WORDS AND THESE
ACTIONS AND... THINK ABOUT A
DECISION.
>> Jeff: WELL, ONCE AGAIN, WE
GO INTO A VOTE WITH A LOT OF
UNCERTAINTY.
LET'S TRY TO CLEAR IT UP.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CANNOT VOTE FOR SKUPIN.
ANYBODY ELSE, FAIR GAME.
ARTIS, YOU'RE UP.
>> I'M NOT SENDING YOU HOME
BECAUSE YOU'RE A RETURNING
PLAYER.
I'M SENDING YOU HOME BECAUSE
YOU'RE REALLY GOOD AT THIS GAME
AND I RESPECT THAT.
>> I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT ABI IS
NEVER GOING TO GIVE YOU HER
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND WANT TO PLAY TNOW WOULD
BE THE TIME TO DO SO
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTE ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ARTIS.
PENNER.
ARTIS.
TWO VOTES ARTIS.
PENNER.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES ARTIS, TWO VOTES
PENNER.
THAT'S THREE VOTES PENNER.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES PENNER.
ARTIS.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ARTIS.
WE'RE TIED.
FOUR VOTES PENNER, FOUR VOTES
ARTIS.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY, ARTIS.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ARTIS, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
ONCE AGAIN, THIS GAME JUST
TURNED.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff:Next time on
"Survivor":
SKUPIN HAS A PLAN TO STEAL LISA
FROM HER ALLIANCE.
>> YOU AND ME IN THE FINAL FOUR.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: BREAKING UP WITH
ABI IS HARD TO DO.
>> I CAN'T BE IN AN ALLIANCE
WITH SOMETHING WHO DOESN'T TRUST
ME.
>> BUT YOU STARTED THE GAME WITH
US.
>> I DID.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN GOOD AT
BREAKUPS.
>> WELL PLAYED FOR PENNER.
HE MANAGED TO PULL OFF THE
IMPROBABLE.
WELL-PLAYED.
ALL I CAN DO IS APPLAUD HIM.
I HAVE NO ILL WILL TOWARD
ANYBODY IN THE GAME BECAUSE WHEN
IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE, IT IS A
GAME.
I COULD NOT HAVE BEEN MORE
HAPPY.
I TAKE THAT BACK.
YES I COULD HAVE, IF I HAD WON
THE MILLION DOLLARS.