>> Jeff: SURVIVOR IT'S
TOUGHEST, AND MOST DANGEROUS
REALITY COMPETITION OF ALL TIME
"SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES" BROUGHT
BACK THREE PLAYERS THAT PROVED
IT.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: EACH HAD BEEN
MEDICALLY EVACUATED FROM THEIR
PREVIOUS SEASON.
FROM "FANS VERSUS FAVORITES,"
JONATHAN PENNER.
>> I GOT INJURED IN A CHALLENGE.
>> THE INFECTION GOES INTO YOUR
BLOODSTREAM IS POTENTIALLY
FATAL.
>> IT WAS AWFUL.
>> Jeff: FROM SEASON TWO,
AUSTRALIA, MICHAEL SKUPIN.
>> THE WORLD THOUGHT ME FALLING
IN THE FIRE WAS MY GREATEST
FAILURE.
I DIDN'T SEE IT THAT WAY BUT I'M
IN LOVE WITH THE FACT THAT I'M
ABLE TO COME OUT HERE AND DO IT
AGAIN.
>> Jeff: AND RUSSELL SWAN FROM
"SURVIVOR: SAMOA."
>> THE LAST TIME I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR" IT SMACKED ME IN THE
CHOPS.
THIS TIME I'M SMACKING BACK.
>> Jeff: IN ADDITION TO THE
RETURNING PLAYERS, THE CASTAWAYS
WERE JOINED BY TWO FAMILIAR
SUPER FANS, FORMER BASEBALL STAR
JEFF KENT.
>> I PLAYED IN THE WORLD SERIES
WITH BASES LOADED.
I'VE SEEN PRESSURE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A CHALLENGE
FOR ME, NO DOUBT.
AND I'M HOPING PEOPLE WON'T
RECOGNIZE ME.
>> Jeff: AND FORMER TEEN TV
STAR LISA.
>> I PLAYED BLAIR WARNER ON "THE
FACTS OF LIFE."
BLAIR WOULD NEVER IN A MILLION
YEARS BE ON "SURVIVOR," BUT I'M
VERY, VERY DIFFERENT, AND AT
THIS POINT I'M GETTING TO BE
JUST LISA.
>> Jeff: FROM THE BEGINNING
THESE THREE TRIBES WERE HIT BY A
STORM THAT LASTED 21 DAYS.
>> COME ON, RAIN, STOP.
>> Jeff: THE RAIN NEVER LET
UP.
FOOD SOURCE WERE SCARCE.
>> I DO DO ANYTHING FOR FOOD
RIGHT NOW.
AT LEAST GIVE ME HOPE.
>> Jeff: AND TO MAKE MATTERS
WORSE-- MALCOLM AND DENISE STILL
STRUG LING OUT IN THE WATER.
MAT SING NEVER WON A CHALLENGE.
AFTER FOUR LOSSES IN A ROW.
>> I DON'T GET WHAT'S HAPPENING,
FARTHER.
>> Jeff: THE FIRST RETURNING
PLAYER WAS SENT HOME.
MALCOLM AND DENISE-- YOU'RE DOWN
TO TWO, YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'VE GOT
TO DO-- WERE THE ONLY ONE TO
SURVIVE.
THE UNLIKELY DUOHAD BEEN IN AN
ALLIANCE SINCE DAY ONE.
>> INSTANTLY, WE JUST CLICKED.
>> Jeff: AND WERE INSEPARABLE
UNTIL THE GAME SPLIT THEM UP.
MAT SING HAS BEEN DECIMATED.
MAT SING IS NO MORE.
WE HAVE TWO TRIBES NOW.
MALCOLM GOES TO TANDANG.
DENISE GOES TO KALABAW.
>> I'M STILL HOLDING THAT TRUST
THAT IT'S MALCOLM AND I, AND THE
TIME COMES I GO BACK WITH
MALCOLM.
>> Reporter: AT TANDANG, LISA
WAS DISCOVERING THE REAL FACTS
OF LIFE.
>> IT'S HARD BEING ON THE
OUTSIDE.
MAYBE I'M NOT ABLE TO PLAY THIS
GAME.
>> Jeff: SHE STRUGGLED TO FIT
IN WITH HER YOUNG TRIBE.
>> SHE'S JUST, LIKE, AN
OUTSIDER.
>> I DON'T TRUST HER.
SHE'S A SMART PLAYER.
DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE LISA.
>> Jeff: AND HER ONLY BOND WAS
WITH SKUPIN.
>> LISA IS MY CLOSEST ALLY OUT
HERE.
>> YOU WOULD HAVE NO REASON TO
THINK I WOULD LIE TO YOU.
>> I AM YOUR FRIEND.
>> ME TOO.
>> BUT IF YOU ( BLEEP ) WITH ME,
YOU'RE DEAD.
>> ANY CHAOS I CREATE IS GOING
TO BE BENEFICIAL TO ME.
>>UN WHAT YOU DID?
>> I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> STOP, DON'T EVEN TRY.
>> SHUT-- SHUT UP.
>> Jeff: WINNING WAS THE ONLY
THING THAT KEPT TANDANG FROM
FALL APART.
AND LISA DONE DOES IT!
TANDANG WINS!
TAN BANG WINS IMMUNITY BY
SECONDS!
AT KALABAW, JEFF KENT LED THE
CHARGE TO TAKE OUT THEIR TRIBE
18 RETURNING PLAYER, JONATHAN
PENNER.
>> DO WE WANT A VETERAN TO WIN
OR DO WE WANT ONE OF US TO WIN?
>> I AGREE.
>> Jeff: BUT PENNER'S IDOL AND
EXPERIENCE IN THE GAME KEPT HIM
ALIVE.
>> I HAVE THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
I'M GOING TO DANCE ALL THE WAY
TO THE MILLIONS.
>> "CONGRATULATIONS!
THE TRIBES ARE MERGING!
>> Jeff: UNFORTUNATELY FOR
PENNER AND KALABAW, THEY WENT
INTO THE MERGE DOWN IN NUMBERS.
>> TO OUR NEW TRIBE.
>> Jeff: WITH THE TRIBES
MERGED, MALCOLM AND DENISE WERE
REUNITED WHILE LISA AND SKUPIN
FINALLY MADE THEIR ALLIANCE
OFFICIAL.
THESE TWO ALLIANCES CAME
TOGETHER.
>> FINAL FOUR.
>> FIANT OF FINAL FOUR.
>> Jeff: AND WERE THE ONLY
CONSTANT IN THE MOST
UNPREDICTABLE SEASON "SURVIVOR"
HAS EVER SEEN.
( GROWLING ).
>> Jeff: WOW.
THERE WERE BLOW-UPS.
>> GET HIM THE ( BLEEP ) OUT OF
HERE.
>> Jeff: BREAK-UPS.
>> I CAN'T BE IN AN ALLIANCE
WITH SOMEONE WHO REALLY DOESN'T
TRUST ME.
>> Jeff: BREAKDOWNS.
YOU'RE PULLING YOURSELF OUT OF
THE GAME?
>> I CAN'T STAY HERE.
>> Jeff: BLINDSIDES.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: PENNER.
JEFF.
>> THIS GAME SUCKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: AND THINGS WE'VE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
36 DAYS LATER-- THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN-- HAVING BEATEN ALL THE
ODDS, THESE FOUR SURVIVORS, TWO
PAIRS, ONE UNLIKELY ALLIANCE ARE
ALL THAT REMAIN.
SKUPIN, ONE OF "SURVIVOR'S"
BIGGEST STARS ALIGN WITH LISA,
AMERICA'S FORMER TEEN STAR.
LISA'S BATTLE THE THE GAME AND
HERSELF TO MAKE IT THIS FAR.
>> TO PLAY THE GAME, I HAVE TO
GO AGAINST EVERYTHING THAT'S
INSIDE ME.
BUT I'M PLAYING TO WIN.
SO BRING IT ON.
>> Jeff: CAN SKUPIN KEEP HIS
GAME AND LISA FROM FALLING
APART?
>> YOU YOU AND I ARE NOT
GUARANTEED IN PHENYL THREE.
>> SECOND OR THIRD THAT THE
STAGE OF THE GAME MEANS NOTHING
TO ME.
>> CAN THE SURSAYS OUTWIT,
OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
THERE'S NOTHING IN THERE THIS
SAYS OUT-KEEP YOUR WORD.
>> Jeff: DENISE AND MALCOLM,
THE ULTIMATE UNDERDOGS, IN A
"SURVIVOR" FIRST, DENISE HAS
GONE TO EVERY SINGLE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AND SURVIVED.
>> I AM ONE IT STUBBORN,
DETERMINED WOMAN.
THE TASTE OF BLOOD IS IN THE
WATER.
I'M GOING TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, THE GOLDEN
BOY, HAS PLAYED A FLAWLESS GAME,
FINDING AN IDOL, AND DOMINATING
CHALLENGES.
( CHEERS )
>> THERE'S A LOT ON THE LINE
HERE.
THERE'S NO REASON TO HOLD BACK
ANY MORE.
WE'RE IN THE HOME STRETCH.
IT'S GO BIG OR GO HOME TIME FOR
ME.
>> Jeff: BUT CAN DENISE TRUST
MALCOLM'S LOYALTY?
>> THIS IS IT, FINAL THREE,
BABY!
WHOOO!
>> Jeff: WILL THESE POWERHOUSE
PLAYERS DESTROY THE COMPETITION
OR EACH OTHER?
IT ALL COMES TO AN END TONIGHT.
FIND OUT WHO WILL CLAIM THE
MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE AND THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> I FEEL LIKE ALIVE.
>> OH, DON'T YOU?
>> THAT'S LIKE HAVING A TUMOR
REMOVED.
>> IT WAS.
NEGATIVE GONE.
>> WHEN DO WE DANCE?
>> NOW.
READY?
>> GETTING RID OF ABI, IT'S THE
BEST FEELING I'VE HAD SINCE I'VE
BEEN OUT HERE.
IT SUCKED LIFE OUT OF YOU HAVING
HER HERE.
I HAVE NEVER MET ANYBODY LIKE
THAT BEFORE.
I MEAN, I'M NOT HAPPY FOR HER
LOSS.
I'M JUST HAPPY FOR OUR PEACE.
>> SHE WAS JUST FULL OF FIRE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'D CALL IT
FIRE.
>> FULL OF...
SOMETHING.
>> ON THE ONE HAND IT'S A REALLY
GOOD THING THAT ABI IS GONE.
THE BAD NEWS IS SHE WENT OUT
WITH A BANG.
WHENEVER SOMEBODY WANTS TO GO
OUT WITH A BANG IN THIS GAME
THEY TEND TO THROW ME UNDER THE
BUS WITH COMPLILTS OF ALL
THINGS.
"MALCOLM WILL DEFINITELY WIN THE
GAME.
MALCOLM IS A LOCK IF HE GETS TO
THE END."
I THINK THEY'RE TRYING TO BE
NICE BUT THE AMOUNT OF DAMAGE
CONTROL I HAVE TO KEEP DOING
AFTER SOMEONE BLOWS UP AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL IS GETTING RIDICULOUS.
>> NOTHING'S CHANGED SINCE TWO
WEEKS AGO.
>> SO NO MATTER WHAT, IT'S ME
AND YOU TOMORROW?
>> MALCOLM AND I HAVE A
"SURVIVOR" ALLIANCE, BUT THE
DECISION I HAVE TO MAKE FOR THE
END GAME STRATEGY HAS TO BE WHO
I WANT TO SIT NEXT TO IN THE
FINAL THREE.
THERE IS A FEELING THAT
MALCOLM'S THE RUNAWAY.
ABI SEES IT THAT WAY.
LISA SEES IT THAT WAY.
I DON'T SEE IT THAT WAY.
I BELIEVE I HAVE A BETTER STORY
THAN HE HAS.
I HAVE TO STEP OUTSIDE THE GAME
FOR JUST A MINUTE AND LOOK AT IT
FROM AN OUTSIDE OBSERVER IN
ORDER TO TRULY MAKE THE DECISION
ON THAT.
>> TREE MAIL!
WE GOT SOMETHING GOING ON.
>> WOW!
>> OKAY.
OH, NO.
>> UH-OH.
>> WHAT?
>> NO WAY.
"WINNING THIS SEX CHALLENGE WILL
BE WORTHY OF YOUR BRAGIN'.
WE'LL HAVE A BETTER SHOT AT THE
MONEY WHEN YOU'VE FINISHED OFF
THE DRAGON."
IS THAT REWARD OR IMMUNITY?
>> WE NEVER KNOW.
>> NO.
>> OH, WE HAVE A CHALLENGE TODAY
WHICH WE WEREN'T EXPECTING.
MY FEAR IS I WILL BE THE NEXT
ONE TO GO.
WE'VE HAD THIS SOLID FOUR BUT
FOUR CAINT GO TO THREE SO I AM
DESPERATE TO WIN IT BECAUSE ONE
OF US IS GOING TO GET THE SHORT
END OF THE STICK, AND I
DEFINITELY DON'T WANT IT TO BE
ME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
FOUR PEOPLE LEFT.
MALCOLM, HOW YOU DOING?
>> I'M GOOD.
YOU KNOW, YOU KNOWLEDGE ABOUT
THIS FOR SO LONG, EVEN BEFORE WE
HIT THE BEACH ON DAY ONE, AND TO
ACTUALLY GET HERE NOW, IT'S
EXCITING.
BUT IT'S NOT OVER YET.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU WILL RACE THROUGH
A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
COLLECTING BAGS ALONG THE WAY.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THREE BAGS,
YOU WILL USE THE PIECES TO SOLVE
A DRAGON PUZZLE.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR.
>> ABSOLUTE!
>> YES.
>> Jeff: IT IS THE BIGGEST
REWARD OF THE GAME.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF TODAY'S
CHALLENGE WINS AN ADVANTAGE IN
THE FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
TOMORROW.
>> OH!
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: FOR 37 DAYS, YOU HAVE
BATTLED WITH ONE GOAL IN MIND--
GETTING TO THE END FOR A SHOT AT
THE MONEY.
WINNING TODAY'S CHALLENGE COULD
MEAN THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
SITTING IN THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL OR BEING THE EIGHTH AND
FINAL JURY MEMBER.
BIG STAKES.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR AN ADVANTAGE IN THE FINAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
EVERYBODY GETS ACROSS THE
BALANCE BEAM QUICKLY.
MALCOLM AND SKUPIN OVER THE
BAMBOO FIRST.
LISA AND DENISE RIGHT BEHIND.
EVERYBODY OFF TO A VERY FAST
START.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR KNOTS
NOW.
THAT FIRST BAG OF PIECES, ONCE
YOU'RE UNTIED MAKE YOUR WAY
THROUGH THE BAMBOO.
DENISE WHIPPING THROUGH THESE
KNOTS.
SKUPIN'S UNTIED.
MALCOLM IS UNTIED.
LISA'S NOW UNTIED.
KEEP MOVING!
THREE PEOPLE THROUGH.
LISA GOING UP TOP AND IT'S
TAKING A LOT LONGER.
MALCOLM FALLS OFF.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
LISA'S THROUGH NOW.
SHE'S IN IT.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THAT SECOND
BAG.
THERE ARE THREE BAGS TOTAL.
SKUPIN HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
SKUPIN HEADING FOR THAT THIRD
AND FINAL BAG.
DENISE HAS HERS UNTIED.
MALCOLM HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
HE'S ACROSS.
LISA STILL STRUGGLING.
MALCOLM UP THE ROPE QUICKLY.
DENISE UP THE ROPE.
HERE COMES LISA.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR THIRD
AND FINAL BAG.
SKUPIN HAS HIS.
HE'S DOWN FIRST.
DENISE RIGHT BEHIND.
START WORKING ON THAT PUZZLE.
MALCOLM'S THERE NOW.
LISA HAS HER THIRD BAG.
SHE'S HEADING DOWN.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLE.
WE'RE BUILDING A DRAGON IN THIS
EVERYBODY FIGHTING FOR A HUGE
REWARD.
ADVANTAGE IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
THIS COULD BE A MILLION-DOLLAR
CHALLENGE RIGHT HERE.
DENISE OFF TO A FAST START.
SKUPIN TRYING TO FIGURE IT OUT.
DENISE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
LISA WITH A PIECE.
MALCOLM WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
DENISE IN THE THE LEAD RIGHT
NOW.
LISA NOW STARTING TO PICK UP THE
PACE.
SHE PLACES ANOTHER PIECE.
SKUPIN STRUGGLING ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
PIECES FALLING OUT.
DENISE MAKING A LOT OF HEADWAY.
MALCOLM WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
LISA STILL FIGHTINGLY.
SKUPIN OUT OF IT RIGHT NOW.
IT WOULD BE SO NICE TO HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE IN THAT FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
HISTORICALLY ADVANTAGES HAVE
WORKED OUT VERY WELL FOR THE
PEOPLE WHO HAVE THEM.
QUITE OFTEN IT RESULTS IN A
VICTORY.
IT IS MALCOLM AND DENISE
FIGHTING FOR AN ADVANTAGE IN THE
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
IT IS VERY CLOSE.
LISA FALLING OUT OF IT.
SKUPIN'S BEEN OUT OF IT.
MALCOLM NOW PLACES ANOTHER
PIECE.
ANDOTHER.
AND ANOTHER.
HE HAS FOUR PIECES LEFT.
DENISE TRYING TO CATCH UP.
MALCOLM IS VERY CLOSE.
MALCOLM WINS REWARD, AN
ADVANTAGE IN THE FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
>> AH!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, COME ON
OVER.
ADVANTAGE IN THE FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
IT IS SEALED.
KEEP IT THAT WAY.
YOU'LL REVEAL THE CONTENTS AT
THE CHALLENGE.
COULD HAVE BEEN A MILLION-DOLLAR
VICTORY TODAY.
>> HOPEFULLY GLAJ.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU GUYS TOMORROW FOR YOUR
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> EXHAUSTED AFTER THAT.
>> YOU ARE GOOD AT PUZZLES.
DANG IT!
NICELY DONE.
>> WE DID NOT NEED MALCOLM
WINNING AN IMMUNITY ADVANTAGE.
HE WAS ALREADY A HUGE THREAT TO
WIN.
JUST ON HIS OWN.
SO IT WAS GOING TO BE AN UPHILL
CLIMB JUST BATTLING MALCOLM.
NOW BATTLING MALCOLM WITH AN
ADVANTAGE.
FORGET IT.
>> GOOD CHALLENGE.
>> TODAY, I MANAGED TO PULL IT
OUT.
I WON SOME SORT OF ADVANTAGE IN
THE THE FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
WHICH IS HUGE.
IT'S THE LAST CHALLENGE, AND AT
THIS POINT I'LL TAKE ANY
ADVANTAGE I CAN GET.
>> ALL RIGHT, I NEED TO GET
WATER.
>> YOU WANT TO GO UP THERE?
>> YEAH, I'LL GO WITH YOU.
EVERYTHING IS GOING EXACTLY AS I
PLAN.
I HAVE THE FINAL THREE DEAL WITH
LISA AND SKUPIN.
I THINK I CAN BEAT THEM AT THE
END.
I ABSOLUTELY THINK I COULD BEAT
DENISE AT THE END, BUT SHE'S THE
HARDEST PERSON TO BEAT FOR ME
RIGHT NOW.
HER STORY IS SIMILAR TO MINE.
THE PEOPLE FROM THE TRIBE THAT
WAS WIPED OUT MADE IT TO THE
END.
I FEEL BAD FOR HER BUT I NEED TO
GO TO THE FINAL THREE WITH
PEOPLE I CAN BEAT.
>> YOU KNOW THAT.
>> MY HEART IS STILL IN MY CHEST
GOING LIKE THIS.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU-- YOU HAVE A
HUGE SHOT AT WINNING IMMUNITY
TOMORROW.
I KNOW YOU'RE STILL THING, BUT
WE NEED TO SOLIDIFY THREE.
I'LL MAKE MY PROPOSAL FOR ME.
I WANT TO BE IN THAT FINAL
THREE.
ARE YOU WILLING TO COMMIT AT ALL
WITH ME?
OR AT THE VERY LEAST MAKE IT A
TIE SO LISA AND I HAVE TO MAKE
FIRE?
>> WELL, NO, JUST MAKE A
DECISION AND JUST GO WITH IT.
I'M DEFINITELY OVERTHINKING IT
BUT I WON'T DO THIS TO YOU
BECAUSE I KNOW I'M BEING AWFUL.
>> I TRIED TO APPROACH MALCOLM
ABOUT GOING TO THEIFIABLE FINAL
THREE TOGETHER, AND HE'S JUST
VERY HESITANT TO MAKE ANY KIND
OF COMMITMENT, SO FOR ME,
KNOWING HE HAD PLANNED SO HARD
TO MAKE SURE WE HAD A SIX, AND
PLANNED TOW HARD TO MAKE SURE WE
HAD A FOUR, MAKES ME VERY LEERY
ABOUT HIS THOUGHTS ON KEEPING ME
IN THE FINAL THREE.
SO THIS IS KIND OF SCRAMBLE
TIME.
I NEED TO FIGURE OUT A PLAN AND
FIGURE IT OUT FAST.
>> I HAVEN'T GOTTEN AN
OPPORTUNITY JUST TO TALK TO
EITHER OF YOU.
AND SO I WANTED TO FEEL YOU
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW WHERE
MALCOLM'S HEAD IS.
I'M GETTING FLASH BACKS TO
PENNER.
LIKE, "MALCOLM, ARE YOU ABLE TO
MAKE ANY COMMITMENT FOR FINAL
THREE?"
"WE'VE GOT TIME.
WE DON'T NEED TO WORRY ABOUT
THAT YET, JUNGLE MOM."
AND I'M LIKE, THAT'S ALL I NEED
TO KNOW.
>> I'M SO GLAD TO HEAR YOU
TALKING LIKE THIS.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE LIKE THIS--
>> WE HAVE BEEN BUT
STRATEGICALLY HE HAS VOTES ALL
OVER THE JURY.
HE HAS THE PHYSICAL GAME.
HE HAS THE SOCIAL GAME.
IF YOU GUYS ARE ON BOARD, IT IS
POSSIBLE.
>> PERFECT.
TODAY HAS BEEN A GOOD DAY.
I JUST FOUND OUT DENISE IS
WILLING TO TURN ON MALCOLM AND
GO TO THE FINAL THREE WITH MIKE
AND ME.
SHE REALIZES SHE DOESN'T HAVE A
CHANCE AGAINST HIM.
NONE OF US DO.
SO THIS IS FABULOUS.
MALCOLM IS THE KIND OF GUY WHO
WILL PUT HIS ARM AROUND YOU, AND
STAB YOU.
>> STAB YOU.
>> THEN VISIT YOU AT THE
HOSPITAL THE NEXT DAY.
AND YOU GET OUT OF THE HOSPITAL
AND SAYING, "WAS THAT THE
SWEETEST THING FOR HIM TO COME
VISIT.
HE'S SUCH A NICE GUY!
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE ALL HAVE BETTER ODDS TOGETHER
UP THERE VERSUS LET'S JUST LET
HIM DO A CLEAN SWEEP.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> OH!
>> SO GLOOD TO HEAR YOU THINKING
LIKE THIS.
I HUGGED HER, BIG HUG.
DIDN'T SHAKE HER HAND.
DIDN'T GIVE HER MY WORD BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SKUPIN IS
GOING TO THINK ABOUT THIS.
>> SO I TALKED TO LISA AND I'M
VOTING FOR MALCOLM.
100%.
>> REALLY?
YEAH, SHE'S LIKE, "I'M SO
RELIEVED."
ALL RIGHT, I JUST WANT TO GO
COOL OFF AND CLEAN UP.
>> YEAH, ENJOY.
>> I WILL.
THANK YOU!
>> DENISE WAS THRILLED WITH YOUR
CONVERSATION.
>> GREAT, ME, TOO.
YOU AND I NEED TO GET OFF AND
DECIDE DEFINITELY WHICH WAY WE
WANT TO GO.
BECAUSE AT THIS POINT, I'M
LEANING TOWARDS GOING TO THE END
WITH DENISE.
>> LISA AND I HAVE A PACT WITH
MALCOLM TO GO INTO THE FINAL
THREE TOGETHER, BUT NOW IT LOOKS
LIKE WE HAVE THE SAME DEAL WITH
DENISE, WHICH IS GREAT BECAUSE
EITHER WAY LISA IS I WILL BE IN
THE FINAL THREE WITH ONE OF
THOSE TWO, DEPENDING ON WHO WINS
IMMUNITY.
IF SHE WINS TOMORROW, THEN WHAT?
>> I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE A
SCENARIO WHERE MALCOLM DOESN'T
WIN IMMUNITY.
>> BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I WAS
THINKING?
IN THE PHYSICAL CHALLENGE I BEAT
MALCOLM TODAY TO THE PUZZLE.
I BEAT HIM IN EVERY PHYSICAL
CHALLENGE.
SO I CAN BEAT HIM.
I'M NOT SAYING I WILL.
I'M SAYING I THINK I CAN BEAT
HIM.
YOU KNOW, THE WORD ON THE STREET
IS MALCOLM'S UNBEATABLE, AND HE
MAKES IT TO THE FINAL THREE,
IT'S A LANDSLIDE, HE'LL GET
EVERY VOTE.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I CAN BEAT MALCOLM.
AND I THINK I CAN TELL A PRETTY
GOOD STORY AT THE END.
SO I JUST HAVE TO KEEP MY COOL
AND FIGURE OUT WHO I WANT TO SIT
NEXT TO IN THE FINALLY BECAUSE
THAT'S THE MILLION-DOLLAR
QUESTION RIGHT THERE.
A CRAZY DAY.
DENISE IS REALLY WORKING IT,
RIGHT?
WE CAN'T CONTROL JURY VOTES BUT
WE CAN CONTROL WHERE WE SIT.
SO WE JUST CAN'T LET HER WIN.
SHE HASN'T WON ANYTHING--
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN WE CAN'T LET
HER WIN.
WE HAVE TO LET HER WIN.
SHE'S THE ONE WE HAVE A BETTER
CHANCE OF BEATING.
SHE HASN'T PLAYED THE GAME.
SHE LET MALCOLM PLAY FOR HER.
I USED TO HATE IT WHEN ABI SAID
I NEED TO KEEP MIKEOLE A LEASH
BUT I THINK YOU NEED TO BE LEVEL
HEADED TO BE ABLE TO MAKE
STRATEGIC MOVES, AND SOMETIMES
SKUPIN IS NOT THAT LEVEL HEADED.
>> REALISTICALLY, WE CAN'T LET
EITHER ONE OF THEM WIN.
>> RIGHT.
>> THEN WE CONTROL THE OUTCOME
OF WHAT HAPPENS IN THE FINAL
PART OF THE GAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> LISA AND I ARE NOT ON THE
SAME PAGE AS FAR AS WHO SITS IN
THE FINAL THREE, AND WHO THAT
LAST PERSON IS ON THE JURY.
SO IF I WANT TO CONTROL THE
OUTCOME OF THE GAME, I HAVE TO
HAVE IMMUNITY IN MY HAND SO I
CAN CREATE THE FINAL THREE
INSTEAD OF JUST FALLING INTO THE
FINAL THREE.
>> TREE MAIL.
>> "CONGRATULATIONS FINAL FOUR.
YOU ARE ALMOST AT THE END.
FOLLOW THE MAP TO THE HEAD LAND.
THERE YOU WILL FIND THE TORCHES
OF YOUR FALLEN COMRADES.
AT EACH TORCH YOU WILL CLCT A
REPRESENTATIVE NAME PLATE OF
THOSE VOTED OUT BEFORE YOU, PAIK
RESPECT TO EACH THEIR MEMORIES
AS THEY EACH HAD A PART IN
GETTING YOU TO THIS POINT.
YOU WILL THEN HEAD TO YOUR FINAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE."
>> THAT'S A FUN DAY.
VERY COOL.
>> THAT'S A BIG ONE.
TREE MAIL WAS BIGGER THAN USUAL.
WE ARE GOING TO DO THE FALLEN
COMRADES TODAY, WHERE YOU PAY
RESPECTS TO EVERYONE WHO HAS
FALLEN BEFORE YOU IN THE GAME.
IT'S A COOL THING TO TAKE THE
TIME AND GO REMEMBER THEM ONE
LAST TIME BEFORE THE BLOOD
STARTS FLOWING TONIGHT.
>> ZANE.
WAS A CRAZY GUY.
HE QUIT SMOKING DAYS BEFORE HE
CAME OUT HERE, GAINED 30 POUNDS,
WAS ALSO ONE OF THE FUNNIEST
GUYS.
>> APPEARED TO BE A LITTLE
INSANE.
PUT IT THAT WAY.
>> I THINK IT WAS VERY STUPID
FOR MY TRIBE TO VOTE ME OUT.
THAT MADE A MOVE WAY TOO EARLY
IN THE GAME.
IN HINDSIGHT, YOU KNOW HINDSIGHT
IS 20-20.
AS YOU CAN SEE, MY WHOLE TRIBE
FOLDED AFTER I LEFT.
>> OH, ROXY.
I THINK ROX WOULD HAVE TO BE ONE
OF THE PEOPLE WITH THE STRONGEST
CONVICTIONS ABOUT HER BELIEFS
THAT I HAVE EVER KNOWN.
>> SHE WAS A FIGHTER.
SHE WAS A FIGHTER.
>> I KEEP IT REAL AND THAT COULD
HAVE BEEN MY DOWNFALL, KEEPING
IT REAL TOO MUCH GETS YOU OUT
SOMETIMES, BUT I WAS JUST
MYSELF, AND I'M PROUD OF IT.
>> OH, ANGIE.
( LAUGHTER ).
ANGIE WAS MY SLEEPING BUDDY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE TURNED OUT TO BE A LOT
TOUGHER THAN WE ALL JUDGED HER
TO BE.
POOR GIRL, ALL SHE WANTED WAS
SOME COOKIES.
>> A GIRL AFTER MY OWN HEART!
>> BEING DITSY OR BUBBLY,
WHATEVER.
THAT'S JUST PART OF WHO I AM.
I'M NOT A DUMB BLOND BUM I'M NOT
SERIOUS ALL THE TIME OR HARD
CORE.
I'M KIND OF WELL-ROUNDED, I FEEL
LIKE.
>> RUSSELL.
UN, THE LEADER, CAME IN SAYING,
"I DON'T WANT TO BE THE LEADER,
GUYS," BUT HE JUST COULDN'T HELP
IT.
HE WANTED TO WIN THIS GAME SO
BAD.
>> A COG TAIJOUS ENEMY AROUND
CAMP.
>> AND HE WAS THE FIRST
RETURNING PLAYER TO GO.
>> I CAME BACK OUT HERE TO WIN
THIS THING.
HOWEVER, WE GOT OUR BUTTS
KICKED, WORST TRIBE EVER IN THE
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY AND TO GO OUT
FOUR STRAIGHT HUMILIATIONS.
>> DANA.
I THINK SHE COULD HAVE BEEN A
GREAT COMPETITOR, BUT HER BODY
JUST WOULDN'T LET HER STAY IN
IT.
>> I CAN SPEAK ON HER BEHALF,
BEING MEDEVACED FROM THIS GAME,
IT JUST LEAVES A LITTLE HOLE
INSIDE.
>> I DEFINITELY THINK I HAD THE
HEART FOR THE GAME, AND I THINK
AT THE END IT WAS ALL HEART, BUT
I JUST DON'T THINK I COULD HAVE
WENT ON ANY LONGER.
YOU CAN ONLY DO WHAT YOU CAN DO.
>> OH, DAWSON.
DAWSON WAS ANOTHER VERY LIVELY
ADDITION TO THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR."
A LITTLE QUIRKY.
A LITTLE OUT THERE, BUT
DEFINITELY ENTERTAINMENT THAT I
THINK KALABAW NEEDED.
>> I PLAYED TOO PASSIVELY.
THAT'S MY BIGGEST REGRET.
BUT HAVING JEFF PROBST SNUFF MY
TORCH, I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW MUCH
I WAS SALIVATING.
I JUST WANTED TO PUT A WET ONE
SO FAR UP ON HIS LIPS.
IT WAS A MOMENT HE AND I SHARED.
AND I'LL NEVER BE THE SAME.
>> KATIE, GREAT COMPETITOR.
WASN'T AFRAID TO STRATEGIZE.
A LITTLE BIT OF A POTTY MOUTH,
WHICH I LOVED.
I REALLY LIKED KATIE, BUT,
UNFORTUNATELY, SHE HAD TO GO SO
I COULD STAY.
SO THANK YOU, KATIE.
>> THE ONLY TIME I'VE EVER
CAMPED IS WITH GIRL SCOUTS, SO
THE FACT THAT I STUCK IT OUT FOR
16 DAYS IS, LIKE, HUGE TO ME.
>> R.C., MY FIRST ALLIANCE IN
THE GAME, 30 SECONDS INTO THIS
GAME, R.C. WAS ALL OVER IT.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE EXTREME
METHODS OF HER PLAYING BECAME SO
OBVIOUS TO EVERYBODY, SHE
INSTANTLY BECAME A THREAT.
>> I SORT OF WAS OFTRASIGHTS
BECAUSE I TOOK MY CLUE AND THE
IDOL, AND THEN TURNED EVERYONE
AGAINST ME.
YOU KNOW, YOU WIN SOME, YOU LOSE
SOME.
I'M NOT REALLY USED TO LOSING.
( LAUGHS )
>> JEFF.
SORRY TO SEE HIM GO.
HE WAS A GOOD PLAYER.
>> HE WAS THE ONE THAT WANTED
RETURNING PLAYERS GONE THE MOST.
>> GREAT, GREAT ATHLETE.
>> I PLAYED BASEBALL WITH SOME
OF THE MOST SPOILED BRATS YOU
EVER MET.
MAYBE I WAS ONE OF THEM AT
TIMES.
BUT I'M PROUD OF THE FACT THAT I
HAVE BEEN ABLE TO GET THROUGH
THIS GAME WITHOUT PISSING A LOT
OF PEOPLE OFF.
>> ARTIS.
>> VERY, VERY LOYAL TO THE
TANDANG TRIBE.
I THINK ALMOST LOYAL TO A FAULT.
>> TANDANG WAS CAPABLE OF
LITERALLY ANNIHILATING THE OTHER
TWO TRIBES, SO I'M DISAPPOINTED
THAT MY TRIBE COULDN'T STAY
TOGETHER AND DO WHAT WAS TAILOR
MADE FOR US TO DO.
>> PETE.
STUCK WITH ABI THROUGH THICK AND
THIN, AND IT WAS THAT WHICH
REALLY, REALLY BIT HIM IN THE
BUTT IN THE END.
>> I'M DEFINITELY PROUD OF THE
GAME THEY PLAYED.
I WANTED TO BE IN CONTROL.
AND MOST OF THE GAME I WAS IN
CONTROL.
THE TURNING POINT IN THE GAME
WAS I KEPT ABI FOR WAY TOO LONG.
I REALLY DISLIKED HER FROM DAY
ONE, BUT SHE HAD THE IDOL.
I HAD TO STICK WITH HER, AND I
JUST MADE THE WRONG DECISION.
>> PENNER.
ENTERTAINMENT ON STEROIDS.
>> GREAT STRATEGIC PLAYER.
>> NOBODY WANTED TO SIT NEXT TO
HIM.
>> NO.
>> IN THE FIND THREE BECAUSE WE
KNEW HE COULD CREATE A SPEECH
THAT WOULD HAVE KNOCKED
EVERYONE'S SOCKS OF.
>> I LOVE "SURVIVOR" AND I'VE
BEEN ONE OF THE LUCKIEST FEW
PEOPLE IN THE WORLD TO HAVE
GOTTEN THREE OPPORTUNITIES TO
PLAY THIS.
I REGRET NOTHING.
I'VE LEFT EVERYTHING ON THE
FIELD.
YOU KNOW, I GAVE BLOOD, SWEAT,
AND TEARS FOR THIS GAME.
AND I HOLD MY HEAD UP HIGH AT
THIS POINT.
>> WHEN I MET CARTER, I SAW A
YOUNG MAN BECOME A MAN OUT HERE.
AND HIS PHYSICAL STRENGTH AND
HIS PERSONAL CHARACTER IS THE
REASON WE HAD TO WRITE HIS NAME
DOWN.
>> I WAS WHO I SAID I WAS.
I WORK HARD AND I DEVELOPED
SOLID RELATIONSHIPS WITH PEOPLE
OUT HERE.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE,UN, THAT IT
COULDN'T HAVE GOT ME FARTHER.
>> ABI.
OUR LITTLE BRAZILIAN
FIRECRACKER.
>> TUMULTUOUS AND TENACIOUS.
>> I'M SAY THIS FOR THE GIRL--
AS MUCH AS EVERYONE WANTS HER
GONE FOR SO LONG, TO MAKE IT TO
FIFTH PLACE IS PRETTY
IMPRESSIVE.
>> I WAS GENUINELY SURPRISED
THAT PEOPLE DIDN'T LIKE ME SO
MUCH.
I LEARNED A LOT FROM THAT
EXPERIENCE.
AND STILL WENT HOME FIGHTING AND
WITH MY HEAD UP HIGH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOT IT?
OKAY.
THERE IT GOES.
WATCH THE PUPPY BURN.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
MALCOLM.
I GOTTA TAKE IT BACK.
FOR THE LAST TIME, IMMUNITY BACK
UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU EACH
HAVE A QOODEN CYLINDER THAT HAS
BEEN CUT INTO SEVERAL PIECES.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL PICK UP THE
FIRST PIECE USING TWO HANDLES.
YOUR GOAL-- BALANCE A BALL ON
YOUR CENTER PIECE OF WOOD.
EVERY FIVE MINUTES WE'LL ADD
MORE PIECES MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT TO BALANCE THE BALL.
IF AT ANY POINT THE BALL FALLS
OFF THE PIECE OF WOOD YOU'RE OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
YOUR SHOT AT IMMUNITY IS OVER.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEES THEMSELVES
A SPOT AT THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE YOU WILL GET TO
PLEAD YOUR CASE ABOUT WHY YOU
DESERVE THE MILLION DOLLARS.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE ONE OF YOU WILL BECOME THE
FINAL MEMBERst JURY.
AT THE LAST REWARD CHALLENGE,
MALCOLM, YOU BATTLED AND WON AN
ADVANTAGE IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> AND HE DOESN'T NEED IT.
>> "YOU ARE ALLOWED A SECOND
CHANCE IN THIS FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
SHOULD YOU DROP THE BALL AT ANY
POINT, YOU ARE NOT OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE BUT WILL REPLACE THE
BALL AND START AGAIN."
>> OH, WOW.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: THAT MEANS ONE SECOND
CHANCE.
IF AT ANY POINT, MALCOLM DROPS
HIS BALL, HE GETS ONE FREE SHOT
TO PUT IT BACK ON AND KEEP
GOING.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TAKE YOUR
SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
PICKUM YOUR HANDLES.
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO IS PUT
BOTH SIDES OF THE HANDLE AGAINST
THAT FIRST PIECE OF WOOD AND
PICK IT UP.
ALL RIGHT, IN THREE, TWO, ONE,
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS KEEP THAT
BALL BALANCED.
SIMPLE LITTLE BACKYARD GAME
COULD BE WORTH A MILLION BUCKS.
EVERYBODY LOOKS REALLY SOLID
RIGHT NOW.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SURVIVE
ANOTHER 30 SECONDS, AND YOU ARE
SAFE IN THIS ROUND.
MALCOLM WITH A LITTLE BIT OF A
WOBBLE.
A GOOD RECOVERY.
10 SECONDS LEFT.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE,
EVERYBODY SAFE.
SET DOWN YOUR BALL.
RELAX YOUR HANDS.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO ADD TWO MORE
PIECES OF WOOD, ONE ON EITHER
SIDE.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB THEM AND PLACE
THEM.
THIS ROUND WILL BE MORE
DIFFICULT.
ALL RIGHT.
PICK UP YOUR HANDLES.
HERE WE GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE, LIFT.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
THREE PIECES OF WOOD NOW.
A LOT LONGER THROW.
HARD TORE KEEP IT BALANCED.
MALCOLM WITH AN ADVANTAGE.
IF HIS BALL DROPS HE GETS A FREE
RESET.
SKUPIN A LITTLE BIT OF THE
JITTERS.
DENISE, NICE ADJUSTMENT.
LISA ROCK SOLID.
MALCOLM DROPS HIS BALL.
HE IS NOT OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
HE HAS A SECOND SHOT.
EVERYBODY, SET YOUR BALLS DOWN,
AND WE WILL RESET.
MALCOLM'S ADVANTAGE WILL NOW
COME INTO PLAY.
THIS IS HIS ONE OPPORTUNITY FOR
A SECOND SHOT.
AND NOW WE RESUME THIS ROUND.
EVERYBODY PUT YOUR HANDLES ON
THE WOOD.
HERE WE GO.
IN FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
WE ARE BACK ON.
MALCOLM'S SECOND SHOT HAS KEPT
HIM IN THIS CHALLENGE.
NOW EVERYBODY IS ON THE SAME
PAGE.
YOUR BALL DROPS, YOU'RE OUT,
THAT'S IT.
GO HOME.
EVERYBODY VERY SOLID.
EXCEPT MALCOLM.
THAT BALL STILL MOVING AROUND.
ARMS SHAKING.
MALCOLM FLIRTING WITH DISASTER,
BUT STILL ALIVE.
CALM YOUR BODY.
MALCOLM WITH ANOTHER AMAZING
RECOVERY.
BALL IS ALMOST HOPPING IT'S
MOVING SO MUCH.
JUST LIKE THAT, MALCOLM IS OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE, NO SHOT AT
IMMUNITY.
HIS FATE IN THIS GAME WILL NOW
REST IN SOMEBODY ELSE'S HANDS.
MALCOLM HAD AN ADVANTAGE, IT
GAVE HIM A SECOND SHOT, AND IT
DIDN'T MATTER.
HE'S STILL THE FIRST PERSON OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
ONE MINUTE LEFT.
WE MOVE TO THE NEXT ROUND.
SKUPIN VERY STEADY.
LISA STEADY.
DENISE STEADY.
DENISE, GOOD RECOVERY.
30 SECONDS.
DENISE DROPS HER BALL.
DENISE IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
NOW WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
10 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
YOU ARE BOTH SAFE.
SET DOWN YOUR BALLS AND RELAX.
SKUPIN AND LISA SURVIVE ANOTHER
ROUND.
MOVE ON TO ROUND THREE.
TWO MORE BLOCKS OF WOOD HAD BEEN
ADDED.
IT WILL BECOME MUCH MORE
DIFFICULT.
>> COME ON, SKUP.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR HANDLES,
HERE WE GO, THREE, TWO, ONE, AND
LIFT.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
THIS COULD BE THE FINAL ROUND
RIGHT HERE.
WE ARE DOWN TO LISA AND SKUPIN
BATTLING FOR THE FINAL IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
30 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
DIG DEEP RIGHT NOW.
30 SECONDS.
KEEP IT TOGETHER FOR 30 SECONDS.
LISA WITH A TINY WOBBLE.
LISA STARTING TO WOBBLE A LITTLE
MORE.
STILL HAVE 10 SECONDS LEFT IN
THIS ROUND.
SHE'S GOT TO HANG ON.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
YOU'RE BOTH SAFE.
DROP YOUR BALLS.
NICE JOB, GUYS.
>> GOOD JOB, LISA.
>> Jeff: WE MOVE ON TO THE
NEXT ROUND.
WE WILL PLACE TWO MORE PIECES
NOW, MAKING THIS VERY LONG, VERY
TOUGH TO BALANCE.
HERE WE GO.
PICK UP YOUR HANDLES.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
LIFT.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
SKUPIN OR LISA WILL GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT WEARING THE
NECKLACE.
VERY BIG DECISION AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL.
YOU WANT TO BE THE ONE IN
CHARGE.
YOU'RE IN A DANGER ZONE NOW.
ANY MOVEMENT CAN KNOCK THAT BALL
OFF.
SKUPIN ADJUSTING.
SOMETHING'S NOT WORKING, CHANGE
SOMETHING UP.
CHANGE YOUR BREATHING.
CHANGE YOUR FOCUS.
A LITTLE BIT OF MOVEMENT IN
LISA.
THAT'S ABOUT IT.
DON'T THINK ABOUT ANYTHING,
NOTHING, NOTHING, NOTHING BUT
THIS.
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE.
BALANCING THAT LITTLE BALL ON
THESE PIECES OF WOOD IS ALL YOU
SHOULD BE THINKING ABOUT RIGHT
NOW.
LISA DROPS HER BALL.
SKUPIN WINS FINAL IMMUNITY.
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AFTER RETURNING TO A GAME HE
PLAYED 12 YEARS AGO.
SKUPIN WILL GET A CHANCE TO
FINISH WHAT HE STARTED.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> WE MADE IT TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
SKUPIN, SAFE AT TONIGHT'S FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT I'D HEAR YOU
SAY THAT.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE THERE.
YOU ARE SAYE SAFE IN THIS GAME.
YOU HAVE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN
GO.
TONIGHT, TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
MALCOLM, LISA, DENISE, AFTER 38
DAYS IN THE PHILIPPINES, ONE
PERSON WILL BECOME THE FINAL
MEMBER OF OUR JURY, THE OTHER
TWO WILL JOIN SKUPIN AT THE
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR HOW THIS
AFTERNOON GOES.
I'LL SEE YOU ALL TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
>> YOU GUYS DID, OH, MY GOSH.
GOOD TRY, MAN.
YOU TRIED.
>> I JUST HAVE SHAKY HANDS.
THE ADVANTAGE WOULD HAVE HAD TO
HAVE BEEN, "MALCOLM, YOU
AUTOMATICALLY WIN" FOR ME TO PUT
THAT OFF.
I NEEDED TO WIN THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE TO GUARANTEE MY SPOT
FOR THE FINAL THREE BUT THE
MINUTE I GET NERVOUS AROUND A
GIRL OR ANYTHING MY HANDS START
SHAKING AND WHEN I SAW MY HANDS
SHAKING IT GOT WORSE AND WORSE
AND WORSE.
IT'S A DISCONCERTING SCENARIO
BECAUSE MY FATE NOW RESTS WITH
LISA AND SKUPIN.
>> YOU BEAT HIM.
>> RIGHT WHEN WE NEEDED IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I DID IT.
THIS WIN MEANS I MADE TO THE
VERY, VERY, VERY END.
AND WHAT I'M MOST PROUD OF IS
THE FACT THEY ALL SAID THE SAME
THING, MALCOLM IS GOING TO WIN.
IT TURNS OUT IT WAS NOT EVEN
CLOSE.
MR. SKUPIN, WELL DONE.
>> YEAH.
NOW THERE'S A TON OF STRATEGY.
WHO DO YOU KEEP?
WHO DO YOU PUT ON THE JURY?
CAN YOU GET THEIR VOTE?
AND IT'S UP TO ME TO MAKE THAT
DECISION.
>> WE'RE ALL COOL, YES?
I'M SO SCARED.
I'VE HAD A NECKLACE FOR THE PAST
WEEK.
AND I DON'T HAVE ONE.
SHE'S GOING TO WANT YOU ALL TO
THROW VOTES AT ME.
>> SHOULD WE JUST GO ALONG WITH
HER AND SAY YEAH?
>> NO!
>> NO, NO, I'M SAYING TO SAY IT.
>> IF WE'RE ALL GOOD, I DON'T
CARE.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME IN A LONG
TIME IN THIS GAME I HAVEN'T BEEN
CALLING THE SHOTS.
HOPEFULLY, I'VE STRATEGIZEWELL
ENOUGH TO WHERE IT DOESN'T
MATTER.
I HAVE AN OATH FROM LISA AND
SKUPIN THAT THEY'RE WITH ME,
THAT DENISE IS GOING HOME.
BUT PEOPLE ARE OUT HERE PLAYING
A GAME FOR A MILLION DOLLARS,
AND IF THEY GET ANY CRAZY IDEAS
I COULD BE IN FOR A NASTY
SURPRISE TONIGHT.
>> IS THIS A GOOD OPPORTUNITY.
I'M STILL ON BOARD.
ARE WE STILL GOOD?
>> IT'S REALLY.
MEESE LEASA AND I ARE TIGHT,
RIGHT.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND IT'S OUR DECISION BETWEEN
YOU AND MALCOLM.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> SO, OBVIOUSLY, IF YOU'RE ON
BOARD WITH US, THEN IT'S THREE
TO ONE.
>> THEN IT'S THREE TO ONE.
>> IF WE DECIDE TO GO WITH
MALCOLM, THEN, OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE
GONE.
>> I'LL BE GONE.
I KNOW, SO MY PLAN WILL BE
MALCOLM WITH THE HOPES THAT YOU
TWO STAY ON THAT.
I MEAN, I'M 100% ON THAT.
>> YOU WOULD BE SILLY.
>> 100%.
>> TO DO ANYTHING ELSE.
>> I AM SO MAD.
MALCOLM AND I COULD HAVE STAYED
TOGETHER AND SPLIT THE VOTE,
HAVE IT BE A TIE, BUT NOW THAT'S
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
SO MY HEAD IS CLEARLY ON THE
BLOCK TONIGHT.
>> YOU WILL WRITE MALCOLM'S NAME
DOWN.
>> IT'S GUARANTEED.
THE PROBLEM IS SKUPIN IS KIND OF
THE DREAMER GUY.
HIS MIND IS GOING A THOUSAND
DIFFERENT PLACES AND HE MAY NOT
ALWAYS SEE THE REPERCUSSIONS.
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU TAKE THE
BEST OF THE BEST OF THE BEST TO
THE END.
SO I HAVE TO FIGURE ON THE A WAY
TO CONVINCE HIM THAT IT'S WORTH
IT TO TAKE ME WITH THEM.
I'M ONE STUBBORN, DETERMINED
WOMAN.
AND IF I CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN, I'M
GOING TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING, DUDE?
>> YOU KNOW, THERE'S A WEIRD,
INSTINCTIVE, PRIMITIVE SIDE OF
ME THAT SAYS GO AGAINST THE
BEST.
GO AGAINST THE BEST.
>> I KNOW.
>> IS THERE HONOR IN BEATING
MALCOLM OVER BEATING YOU OR
LISA?
IS THERE ANY HONOR IN THAT?
>> I MEAN, THERE IS TO SOME
EXTENT, BUT WILL IT HAPPEN?
AND IS THAT A RISK THAT'S WORTH
TAKING, KNOWING-- IF THE JURY
VOTES WITH MALCOLM, IS THERE
HONOR BEATING HIM?
MY FEAR IS WE WON'T.
>> THE OBVIOUS CHOICE IS VOTE
MALCOLM OUT.
THAT SEEMS LIKE THE OBVIOUS.
BUT WHEN IT COMES RIGHT DOWN TO
IT, I WOULD LOVE TO TAKE MALCOLM
AND BEAT HIM STRAIGHT UP MAN TO
MAN, TWO WARRIORS, FOUGHT TO A
HEAD.
HE WON THREE INDIVIDUAL
CHALLENGES.
I WON THREE INDIVIDUAL
WHAT A GREAT HEAD-TO-HEAD BATTLE
THAT WOULD BE.
>> I HAVE A RESPECT FOR THE TWO
OF YOU.
I JUST FEEL THIS FRIENDSHIP WITH
YOU AND LISA.
I'M GETTING ALL CHOCKED UP.
I SWEAR TO GOD, IT'S NOT A PLOY.
THIS IS NO PLOY.
I REALLY CARE ABOUT BOTH OF YOU,
AND WHATEVER YOU DECIDE I WILL
RESPECT, WHATEVER YOU BOTH
DECIDE.
I FEEL THERE ARE FRIENDSHIPS
THAT HAVE FORMED OUT HERE THAT
WILL SUPERCEDE THIS GAME.
MALCOLM AND I MAY HAVE HAD AN
ALLIANCE, BUT THERE'S A
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THAT AND A
TRUE FRIENDSHIP.
BUT THIS IS ALSO A GAME, AND YOU
HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT'S BEST
FOR YOU GUYS, BUT YOU KNOW WHERE
I'M VOTING.
>> WOW, IT'S SUCH A BIG
DECISION.
>> IT IS.
>> I JUST HEARD YOUR COMRADE
OUT, ALL THE REASONS WHY SHE
SHOULD COME INSTEAD OF YOU.
>> SHE'S SUCH A SWEETHEART.
>> RIGHT NOW I HAVEN'T DECIDED
WHO I'M GOING TO KEEP YET.
I AM STRONGLY CONSIDERING
KEEPING MALCOLM.
YOU KNOW, MY WIFE SAID TO ME AS
I WAS WALKING OUT THE DOOR, MAKE
US PROUD OF YOU."
AND I WOULD LOVE TO GET TO THE
FINAL THREE BY KEEPING MY WORD,
AND BEING HONORABLE, AND COME
THE FINAL VOTE, HAVE HER SAY,
"YOU MADE US PROUD."
>> YOU KNOW, I'VE TOLD YOU HOW I
FEEL.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME ABOUT WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING?
>> RIGHT NOW.
I THINK IT'S MALCOLM IN THE
FINALS.
>> TONIGHT, WE CAN EITHER BRING
MALCOLM OR DENISE TO THE FINAL
THREE.
ASSUMING MICHAEL AND I WILL VOTE
TOGETHER, WHICH IS A BIG
ASSUMPTION BECAUSE SKUPIN IS A
WILD CARD HERE.
>> HE'S GOOD AT THAT.
HANDING THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR ON A PLATTER TO MALCOLM
WOULD JUST BE STUPID.
EVERYBODY WHO SIGNED UP TO PLAY
THIS GAME CAME TO WIN.
AND I DID, TOO.
SO AFTER WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH,
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES TO
MAKE SURE MALCOLM IS NOT IN THE
FINAL THREE.
.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
R.C.
JEFF.
ARTIS.
PETE.
PENNER.
CARTER.
AND ABI, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, 38 DAYS, ONE SPOT LEFT IN
THE JURY, THREE SPOTS AT THE
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SKUPIN, HOW BIG A FACTOR ARE
ALLIANCES AT THIS POINT IN THE
GAME?
>> I MEAN, IT'S A PART OF THE
GAME THAT GETS YOU GOING AND
GETS YOU THROUGH THE MIDGAME AND
GETS YOU TO THE END GAME, AND
IT'S ALWAYS A FACTOR.
YOU HAVE TO WEIGH OUT
EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: DENISE, DOES IT HAVE
ANY IMPACT THAT YOU AND MALCOLM
STARTED THIS GAME TOGETHER AND
SKUPE AND I KNOW LISA STARTED
THIS GAME TOGETHER?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU CAN LOOK AT THOSE ALLIANCES
FROM THE START, AND IS THERE A
LOYALTY THAT YOU HOPE WILL TAKE
YOU INTO THAT FINAL THREE?
DO YOU LOOK AT NEW ALLIANCES
THAT WERE FORMED WITH THE FOUR
THAT GOT US HERE?
AND YOU'RE LOOKING AT EACH LAYER
OF THAT.
YOU KNOW, THE STRATEGY, THE
LOYALTY, THE ALLIANCES.
I MEAN, IT'S A GREAT PLACE TO BE
BUT IT DEFINITELY DOESN'T GET
ANY EASIER.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, GIVEN HOW
YOU STARTED-- YOU AND DENISE
LOSING, LOSING, LOSING, AND YOU
GET SPLIT UP AND SOMEHOW YOU
SURVIVE.
THERE'S CLEARLY SOME SORT OF
LOYALTY TO DENISE BUT IT'S BEEN
COMPLICATED.
>> YEAH, THE STORY LINES GETS
INTERTWINED.
EVERYTHING GETS MIXED UP.
PEOPLE YOU WERE SUPER TIGHT WITH
ON DAY ONE YOU'RE NOT SO TIGHT
WITH AT THE END.
I WAS CLOSE WITH ANGY ON DAY ONE
AND HAD TO CUT HER THROAT
EARLIER THAN I HAD TO CONSIDER
GETTING RID OF DENISE.
>> Jeff: DENISE, THAT HAS TO
GIVE YOU A BIT OF CONCERN.
>> ABSOLUTELY, INCREDIBLY
CONCERNING.
BUT WE'RE LIKE SEPARATED AT
BIRTH, AND WENT ON AND LIVED
DIFFERENT LIVES AND BUILT
DIFFERENT RELATIONSHIPS AND LUCK
OF THE DRAW GOT BACK TOGETHER
AND YOU HOPE THAT THAT LOYALTY
IS THERE, BUT THIS IS
"SURVIVOR."
AND SO ABSOLUTELY I'M CONCERNED.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, YOU COULD
READ DENISES COMMENT TWO WAYS.
>> ANY GUILT I FELT FOR WHAT I
JUST SAID IS GONE NOW.
BUT WE'RE IN AGREEMENT.
WE BOTH HAD TO FORM NEW
RELATIONSHIPS TO SURVIVE IN THIS
GRAHAM.
WHEN WE GOT BACK TOGETHER WE
WORKED TOGETHER AND WORKED
TOGETHER VERY WELL.
IT WAS ALWAYS TO A FINAL FOUR
END AND WE BOTH NEW EXWOOU THAT.
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: IT'S INTERESTING THAT
THERE IS DIVISION HERE, AND YET
OVER HERE WITH LISA AND SKUPIN
IT'S ALWAYS SEEMED SORT OF
HARMONIOUS.
>> ACTUALLY, OUR RELATIONSHIP
HAS BEEN REFERRED TO AS AN "OPEN
RELATIONSHIP," BECAUSE WE HAVE
NOT BEEN TOGETHER ALL ALONG THE
PATH.
WE VOTED SEPARATE WAYS.
WE WANTED TO BE TOGETHER, BUT I
DIDN'T WANT TO VOTE OUT MY
ALLIANCE, AND SO HE WENT WITH
HIS NEW ONE, AND THEN WE KIND OF
RECONNECTED.
SO IT HAS NOT BEEN A TRUE-BLUE
ALLIANCE ALL THE WAY ALONG.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, THAT'S A
LITTLE LIKE UNREQUITED LOVE.
"WE WANTED TO BE TOGETHER BUT
THE FORCES KEPT US APART."
AND SUDDENLY THAT'S TWO VOTES
OVER THERE.
>> THAT WAS A SWEET STORY.
>> YEAH, I CAN'T FIGURE OUT WHAT
GOES ON WITH THOSE TWO.
THAT'S HOW THEY'VE BEEN FOR A
REALLY LONG TIME OUT HERE.
SO THIS LATE IN THE GAME,
READING INTO THAT RELATIONSHIP
IS EXTREMELY DIFFICULT.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN, LET'S TALK
ABOUT FAVORS, LIKE MALCOLM GAVE
YOU THIS GREAT GIFT.
HE LET YOUR SON HAVE THE
"SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE.
HOW BIG OF AN IMPACT WILL THAT
HAVE TONIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW, I TOLD MALCOLM HE'S
GOT FAVORS FOR LIFE.
>> Jeff: LISA, HOW ABOUT YOU.
DO YOU THINK FAVORS WILL PLAY A
PART IN TONIGHT'S VOTE?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD HAVE TO BE A
MILLION-DOLLAR FAVOR.
I DON'T KNOW THAT ANY FAVORS
HAVE BEEN EXCHANGED IN THIS GAME
THAT WOULD BE WORTH A MILLION
DOLLARS OR GIVING UP THE TITLE
OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> Jeff: SO TONIGHT, THIS IS
SIMPLY STRATEGY FOR YOU, GET OUT
THE BIGGEST THREAT TO BEAT ME.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, YOU HAVE TO
BE A LITTLE CONCERNED BECAUSE
YOU'VE GOT A GREAT STORY.
"I WAS ON THE WORST TRIBE.
I WON MY WAY BACK.
I'VE WON SOME CHALLENGES.
I'VE DONE SOME SOLID FAVORS.
SEEM TO BE LIKABLE."
YOU COULD BE THE BIGGEST THEFT.
>> YEAH, I THINK I DO HAVE A
PRETTY COOL STORY IF I MAKE IT
PAST TONIGHT.
BUT DENISE HAS DUN D.N.A. IT ONE
TAD BIG BETTER.
SHE WENT TO EVERY TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
MY HANDS ARE DIRTY AND A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE SITTING OVER THERE
BECAUSE I FLIPPED.
SHE NEVER HAD TO FLOIP ANYBODY.
SHE FLOATED IN THE MIDDLE AND
SHE'S THE ONLY KALABAW HERE SO
DENISE IS FAR AND AWAY MORE
DANGEROUS IN THE FINAL THREE.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN MALCOLM'S
STORY IS VERY CLEAR.
I REALIZE I'M A THREAT.
SHE DWARFS ME.
>> IT'S A STRONG CASE.
MALCOLM AND I, DENISE AND I,
LISA AND I HAVE RUN SCENARIOS
WHAT THE OTHER PERSON WOULD SAY
WHEN IT CAME TO THE FINAL THREE.
EVERYBODY HAS A GREAT STORY.
>> Jeff: LISA, IS THERE A
REASON YOU SHOULD TAKE MALCOLM
TO THE END?
>> DON'T HESITATE THAT LONG.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> THERE'S NOT A REASON FOR ME
TO TAKE HIM TO THE END.
>> Jeff: WOW.
MALCOLM, HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
>> UH-- IT'S, UH, UPSETTING TO
HEAR LISA'S ANSWER.
I'VE LOOKED PEOPLE IN THE EYES
AND SHOOK HANDS AND WE HAVE
DEALS THAT GO BEYOND THIS GAME
AND THAT'S WHAT I'M HOPING TAKES
PRECEDENCE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: WELL, THE ONLY PERSON
WHO FEELS SAFE RIGHT NOW IS
SKUPIN.
LISA, DENISE, MALCOLM, ONE OF
YOU IS ABOUT TO BECOME THE
EIGHTH MEMBER OF THE JURY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DENISE, YOU'RE UP.
>> HEY, MALCOLM, I COMPLETELY
RESPECT THE WAY YOU PLAY THE
GAME, BUT I TRIED TO APPROACH
YOU, AND YOU DIDN'T GIVE ME A
COMMITMENT SO I OUTWIT YOU.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S YOU
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION ISIFIABLE.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE.
MALCOLM.
DENISE.
ONE VOTE DENISE, ONE VOTE
MALCOLM.
TWO VOTES MALCOLM, ONE VOTE
DENISE.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
15th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE EIGHTH AND FINAL MEMBER OF
OUR JURY, MALCOLM.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, DENISE.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> Jeff: I THINK IT'S SAFE TO
SAY THAT IS ONE MORE UNHAPPY
JURY MEMBER YOU CAN ADD TO THE
LIST OF PEOPLE YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO SWAY TOMORROW NIGHT.
THAT'S THE INVOICE FOR DOING
WHAT THEY COULDN'T DO.
YOU MADE IT TO THE END.
THEY DIDN'T.
YOU HAVE A SHOT AT A MILLION
DOLLARS.
THEY DON'T.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE NIGHT UNDER
THE STARS HERE IN THE
PHILIPPINES.
TRY TO ENJOY IT.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT FOR
YOUR FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> MAYBE I PUSHED TOO HARD, I
LEVERAGED TOO MUCH.
I HAD THEM SO DRIVEN TO FINALLY
PLAY THE GAME AND SEE THREATS
THAT THEY FINALLY SAW ME AS A
THREAT.
I'M PISSED OFF THAT I'M NOT
GOING TO BE AT THE END.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S PAINFUL FOR A
LIFELONG FAN.
>> OH, THAT WAS BRUTAL!
>> THAT WAS MY MOST HEART
WREMPING ONE YET.
>> OH, SHE WAS MAD.
HE WAS MAD.
>> YEAH, REALLY MAD.
>> I FEEL BADLY THAT MALCOLM WAS
REALLY UPSET, BUT AT THE SAME
TIME THIS IS THAT PART OF THE
GAME I CAN SAY, MALCOLM, YOU
WERE A GREAT ALLY.
YOU PLAYED A GREAT GAME, BUT
THIS IS THE PART WHERE I OUTWIT
YOU.
HE REALLY SOUND LIKE HE
BELIEVED, LIKE, ABSOLUTELY, HE
WAS GOING TO THAT FINAL THREE.
THITHIS IS THE PART WHERE I WENT
ONE STEP PAST YOU AND YOU CAN BE
ANGRY BUT THAT'S THE GAME.
AS HARD AS THAT WAS, IT STILL
FEELS RIGHT.
>> YOU GOT A LITTLE BIT OF A
VOTE OF CONFIDENCE, THOUGH.
AS HE WAS LEAVING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, MALCOLM SAID
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR MILLION
DOLLARS, DENISE.
MEANING SHE WAS GOING TO RUN
AWAY WITH IT.
I'LL HAVE A LOT TO SAY ABOUT
THAT TOMORROW.
IT'S WEIRD THAT YOU BLINDSIDE
YOUR ALLIANCE FROM DAY ONE, AND
YET YOU GET THE VOTE OF
CONFIDENCE ON THE WAY OUT.
>> BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, THO?
I'M NOT BANKING ON IT.
>> SOME PEOPLE MIGHT NOT WANT TO
VOTE FOR ANY ONE OF US.
I GUESS WHO CAN PLEAD THEIR CASE
THE BEST IS POTENTIALLY THE ONE
WHO IS GOING TO WIN A MILLION
BUCKS.
>> THIS IS THE LAST MORNING
HERE.
I DO WANT TO TAKE IT ALL IN.
>> 39 DAYS.
>> OH!
>> WOW.
>> WOW!
>> TAKE IT ALL IN.
>> I'M GLAD I DIDN'T MISS THIS.
>> IT WAS GREAT TO HIKE UP TO
THE CLIFF THIS MORNING,UN, TO
HAVE THE THREE OF US, AND JUST
TO SIT UP HERE AND HAVE A
DIFFERENT PERSPECTIVE.
>> WHO KNEW THAT IN 39 DAYS SUCH
SIGNIFICANT LIFE CHANGE COULD
HAPPEN.
SUCH DEEP CONNECTIONS COULD BE
BUILT.
>> HERE I AM THIS LITTLE OLD SEX
THERAPIST FROM IOWA, WHO
ACTUALLY HAS PLAYED SOME
STRATEGY.
AND I FEEL LIKE I'M THRIVING OUT
HERE.
>> FROM A GUY WHO HAS BEEN THERE
39 DAYS OF AN ADVENTURE YOU WILL
NEVER, EVER FORGET FOR THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE.
>> LET'S GO CHECK TREE MAIL.
>> I SEE CHAMPAGNE!
>> ORANGE JUICE.
>> ICE N.
>> BUTTER!
>> THIS ISN'T TREE MAIL.
THIS IS TREE MEAL.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> WE WALKED UP TO TREE MAIL
THIS MORNING AND THERE WAS BACON
AND SAUSAGE AND I'LL TELL YOU,
YOUR STRENGTH STARTS TO RETURN
JUST FROM KNOWING YOU'RE GOG
EAT.
I NEVER HAD SAUSAGE LIKE THIS.
OH, I CAN'T GET ENOUGH.
>> OH!
>> WOW!
>> 23 SEASONS I WATCHED THIS
GAME GO.
AND I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED IF I
COULD PLAY THIS WHOLE GAME
STRATEGICALLY ENOUGH TO GET
MYSELF IN THE FINAL THREE.
TO AMAZINGNESS.
>> YES.
FINAL THREE.
>> FINAL THREE.
>> I KNEW I COULD MAKE IT TO THE
END 23 SEASONS AGO.
WHEN I CAME OUT HERE, I TRIED TO
TELL MYSELF THE SAME THING.
BUT THOUGHT OF DOUBT KEPT
CREEPING IN BECAUSE I EVERY TIME
I GOT AROUND A CAMPFIRE I
THOUGHT, DON'T FALL IN THE
SUCKER.
BUT I'M HERE, AND IT FEELS GOOD
TO BE HERE.
>> WOW, THIS HAS BEEN A GREAT
FINAL THREE, THOUGH.
I FEEL REALLY GOOD ABOUT THIS
FINAL THREE.
JUST THE-- THE CAMARADERIE
BETWEEN THE THREE OF US.
>> I LIKE TO THINK THERE'S NO
RUNAWAY.
>> NO, THERE'S NO RUNAWAY.
IT TRULY COULD GO ANY DIRECTION.
YOU KNOW, I LEFT SHOW BUSINESS,
GOT MARRIED, RAISED MY KIDS, AND
THAT WAS A THING OF MY PAST.
AND NOW I'M BACK IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR."
AND YOU WOULD THINK THAT IT
WOULD FEEL VERY SIMILAR, BUT
IT'S NOTHING LIKE WHAT I
EXPERIENCED GROWING UP AS A
CHILD BECAUSE ON THE "FACTS OF
LIFE" I HAD A ROLE.
I HAD A SCRIPT.
I PLAYED A CHARACTER.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> AH!
>> I DIDN'T REALLY REALIZE HOW
MUCH OF YOUR EXPHAERT YOUR SOUL
AND YOUR SPIRIT AND YOUR BODY
ARE INVOLVED IN THIS GAME, THAT
YOUR HEAD IS JUST A LITTLE BITTY
PART OF IT.
AND YET IT'S A HUGE PART OF IT
WHEN IT COMES TO WINNING THE
GAME.
THE OVERWHELMING FEELING IS ONE
OF GRATITUDE.
I MEAN, OF THE 18 THAT STARTED,
THERE ARE ONLY THREE THAT GET TO
EXPERIENCE DAY 39.
THIS IS JUST A RARE PRIVILEGE,
AND I'M VERY AWARE AND HUMBLED
THAT I GET TO EXPERIENCE
SOMETHING SO INCREDIBLE.
>> WOW.
WE DID IT, GUYS.
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
R.C.
JEFF.
ARTIS.
PETE.
PENNER.
CARTER.
ABI.
AND MALCOLM, VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO YOUR FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU HAVE DONE WHAT 15 OTHER
PEOPLE IN THIS GAME COULDN'T
DO-- YOU MADE IT TO THE END.
TONIGHT, THE POWER IN THIS GAME
SHIFTS TO THE JURY.
EIGHT PEOPLE THAT YOU HAD A HAND
IN VOTING OUT NOW HOLD YOUR FATE
IN THEIR HANDS.
THEY WILL DECIDE WHO'S MOST
WORTHY OF THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE MILLION-DOLLAR
CHECK THAT GOES ALONG WITH IT.
YOUR JOB TONIGHT, CONVINCE THEM
IT IS YOU THAT DESERVES IT.
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING TO WORK.
YOU WILL EACH GET TO MAKE AN
OPENING STATEMENT.
THEN THE JURY GETS THEIR CHANCE
TO ADDRESS YOU.
THEN WE VOTE.
OPENING STATEMENTS.
DENISE.
>> LET ME START BY TELLING ALL
OF YOU THE ONE THING I'M NOT
GOING TO DO TONIGHT IS MAKE ANY
APOLOGY FOR BEING A PART OF THIS
FINAL THREE.
I'M NOT ONLY PROUD TO BE HERE
BUT I TRULY FEEL LIKE I DESERVE
TO BE HERE.
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO ADAPT AND
ASSIMILATE NOT JUST IN ONE
TRIBE, TWO TRIBES, BUT THREE
TRIBES.
MY ABILITY TO DO THAT GAVE ME
TIME NOT ONLY TO BUILD INITIAL
ALLIANCES BUT SUB ALLIANCES.
IT GAVE ME TIME TO PROVE TO
DIFFERENT TRIBES I HAD VALUE AND
A RELATIONSHIP TO KEEP ME AROUND
AS A WORKHORSE AT CAMP AND A
VALUE AS STRATEGIST POSITIVE I
WASN'T AFRAID TO MAKE MOVES IN
THE END THAT MAY HAVE UPSET
PEOPLE AND CHANGED THE GAME.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, I'M THE
ONE SITTING UP HERE THAT HAS
SURVIVED EVERY THINK TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
AND I'M STILL SITTING HERE.
I HAVE OUTWIT MANY OF YOU.
I HAVE OUTPLAYED MANY OF YOU.
AND ULTIMATELY, I DID OUTLAST
ALL OF YOU.
AND I BELIEVE THAT I DESERVE THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> Jeff: LISA.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE ALL OUTWITTED,
OUTPLAYED, AND OUTLAST.
WE JUST DID IT IN DIFFERENT
WAYS.
AND IT'S YOURS TO JUDGE WHICH
STRATEGY DESERVES THE TITLE OF
SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE MILLION
DOLLARS.
MY STRATEGY WAS CERTAINLY NOT
PRETTY.
I MEAN, IT WAS BASICALLY RUN
WIDE OPEN AND THEN JUST FALL
DOWN AND THEN GET UP AND DUST
MYSELF OFF, ADJUST, LEARN
SOMETHING, AND RUN SOME MORE.
BUT I DID PLAY MY OWN GAME.
UNFORTUNATELY, ONE OF THE BIG
MISTAKES I FEEL HIKE I MADE WAS
NOT FOLLOWING MY HEART, BUT IT
WASN'T UNTIL MY BROTHER CAME AND
HE SAID, "YOU NEED TO TRUST YOUR
GUT AND REMEMBER THIS IS A
GAME."
AND IT JUST HIT ME.
I HADN'T TRUST MY GUT.
AND I HAD FORGOTTEN IT WAS A
GIM.
AND FROM THAT POINT ON, I
SWITCHED.
I NEEDED TO PLAY THIS GAME
WORTHY OF THE GAME.
IT WOULD BE LIKE BEING IN A
BOXING RING AND BEING AFRAID TO
THROW A PUNCH BECAUSE I MIGHT
HURT SOMEBODY.
AND SO, AT THE END, I FINALLY
GOT IT.
I LEARNED.
I GREW.
AND THREW A PUNCH THAT KNOCKED
OUT THE HEAVIED WEIGHT CHAMPION
OF THIS SEASON, AND SAT ME HERE.
SO I KNOW IT WASN'T A PRETTY
GAME.
BUT I LEARNED, I GREW, AND I'M
PROUD OF THE FINAL GAME THAT I
PLAYED AT THE END.
>> Jeff: SKUPIN.
>> RETURNING PLAYER-- AFTER
WATCHING THE RETURNING SURVIVORS
AND SOME OF THE SUCCESSES, I
STARTED TO THINK I'VE GOT THE
CALL TOO LATE BECAUSE RETURNING
PLAYERS HAVE FOUND SUCCESS IN
THIS GAME, AND EVERYBODY WANTED
RETURNING PLAYERS TO NOT
PROGRESS FARTHER THAN THEY DID.
SO I DID THINGS WITH SUCH #-R
FIRE BECAUSE I KNEW THAT MY BACK
WAS UP AGAINST A WALL MORE SO
THAN ANYBODY OUT HERE.
I THINK I PLAYED MY GUTS OUT.
I MEAN, I GOT PIECES OF MASK
STICKING IN MY FACE.
I HAD TO RESPECT THE CORE OF
THIS GAME.
OUTWIT, OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
I CAN'T PLAY THIS GAME ANY OTHER
WAY.
I LOVE THIS GAME TOO MUCH.
AND I KNOW YOU GUYS DO, TOO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY, NOW
YOUR FIRST OPPORTUNITY TO
ADDRESS LISA, SKUPIN, AND
DENISE.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MOMENT TO GATHER
YOUR THOUGHTS.
AND WE'LL GET ON WITH IT.
LONG TIME FOR THE OPPORTUNITY TO
ADDRESS LISA, SKUPIN, AND
DENISE.
YOUR JOB TONIGHT IS TO GATHER
THE INFORMATION YOU NEED TO MAKE
A VERY BIG DECISION, WHICH ONE
OF THESE THREE IS MOST DESERVING
OF THE TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR
AND THE MILLION DOLLARS THAT
GOES ALONG WITH THE WIN?
LET'S GET STARTED.
ARTIS, YOU'RE UP FIRST.
>> NORMALLY, THIS IS THE PART OF
THE GAME WHERE YOU WOULD BE
CONGRATULATED FOR MAKING IT
WHERE YOU ARE.
UNFORTUNATELY, I CANNOT DO THAT.
BECAUSE IF YOU STARTED THE GAME
WITH THIS HOLY THAN THOU
ATTITUDE, TALKING ABOUT LOYALTY
AND YOU PLAYED A GAME TOTALLY
CONTRADICTORY TO THAT YOU YOU
ARE REAPING WHAT YOU SOW.
IF YOU SAY YOU'RE GOING TO DO
SOMETHING AND DON'T DO IT, YOU
SUFFER THE CONSEQUENCES.
ME?
I MADE ALLIANCES BUT I HELD TRUE
TO ALL OF MY ALLIANCES.
AND THE BEAUTY OF THIS GAME IS,
WHEN IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE,
KARMA IS A BITCH.
>> Jeff: CARTER.
>> WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
>> .
>> HEY, CARTER.
>> LISA, PEOPLE KIND OF LOOKED
TO YOU AS AN EASY TARGET RIGHT
AWAY, AND YET YOU'RE SITTING
HERE.
AND I SAY GOOD JOB FOR THAT.
I TRULY MEAN IT.
SKUPIN, SAME BOAT.
HIT THE BEACH, AND YOUR NAME WAS
TOSSED AROUND MORE THAN
ANYONE'S.
AND YOU DIDN'T GO HOME.
YOU'RE HERE.
I KNOW THERE'S BITTERNESS, AND I
KNOW IT SUCKS BEING UP HERE, THE
PAIN PEOPLE FEEL AND POURING
THAT ON YOU, BUT I DO FEEL LIKE
YOU GUYS PLAYED A GOOD GAME.
SKUPIN, WE WERE REALLY CLOSE,
AND I KIND OF WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOUR THOUGHT WAS ON WHEN YOU
FOUND OUT I WAS GOING HOME.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU
HAVE TO SAY ABOUT THAT.
>> HART T CARTER, I HAVE TO SAY
I CAN'T IMAGINE YOU COULD HAVE
PLAYED THE GAME HARDER.
YOU WERE SO LIKABLE AND SO
SELFLESS.
WHEN WE TALKED ABOUT YOU, THERE
WASN'T ANY REASON TO KEEP YOU IF
ANY OF US WANTED TO HAVE A SHOT.
FRIENDSHIPS AND GAME AT SOME
POINT HAVE TO BE SEPARATED.
AND THE HARD ESTVOTES OUT HERE
ARE A VOTE LIKE WE HAD TO GET
RID OF YOU ONE DAY.
>> THANKS, MAN.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
SERIOUSLY.
>> Jeff: PETE, YOU'RE UP.
>> HI, GUYS.
LISA, I FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE BEEN
HIDING BEHIND THE FACT SAYING,
"I NEVER VOTED FORARTIS.
I NEVER VOTED FOR PETE."
BUT IT'S KIND OF LIKE A JUDAS
SITUATION WHERE YOU KIND OF
DIDN'T VOTE FOR US, BUT YOU KIND
OF KNEW THAT WE WERE GOING HOME.
>> I DID NOT KNOW THATARTIS WAS
GOING HOME.
SO THAT NIGHT I WROTE DOWN
PENNER'S NAME.
I DID NOT KNOW ARTIS WAS THE ONE
THAT WAS IN THE CROSSHAIRS AND I
HAD MADE A DECISION TO NOT GO
WITH THEM, KNOWING IT WOULD COST
ME PROBABLY A MILLION DOLLARS.
SO I'M GLAD I HAD A CHANCE IT
CLEAR THAT UP.
>> OKAY.
DENISE, I'D LIKE TO HEAR WHY
YOUR GAME WAS BETTER THAN
SKUPIN'S AND LISAS AND WHY YOU
DESERVE A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> GOING FROM TRIBE TO TRIBE TO
TRIBE, I THINK I WAS DEFINITELY
FORCED TO PLAY A MUCH MORE
STRATEGIC GAME.
THAT SOCIAL PART OF THE GAME
BECAME VITAL BECAUSE I HAD TO
FIGURE OUT A WAY TO SHOW THAT I
HAD A REASON TO STAY IN THE
TRIBE AIR, REASON TO HELP THEM
STAY STRONG.
GETTING TO THE MERGE, SAME
THING.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN, ALONG WITH
THE REST OF THE KALABAW TRIBE,
WE SHOULD HAVE BEEN THE FIRST
ONES TO GO, NOT R.C.
I MEAN, TRULY, HAD WE COME INTO
THIS TRIBE OF SOLID SEVEN, YOU
GUYS COULD HAVE PICKED US OFF
ONE BY ONE.
BUT THERE WERE FRACTURES, AND I
WORKED WITH THAT.
I WAS FORCED TO BY CHANGING
TRIBES MULTIPLE TIMES.
>> Jeff: THANKS, PETE.
R.C.
>> LISA.
THE WOMAN FROM DAY ONE, SECOND
ONE ON THE RAFT I WANTED OUT
BECAUSE YOU WERE SO SMART AND SO
SORT OF SNEAKY AND SWEET THAT I
KNEW THIS WAS GOING TO HAPPEN.
SO I'M NOT SURPRISED YOU'RE
SITTING HERE BECAUSE I
IDENTIFIED DAY ONE.
AND YOU WERE ABLE TO OUT
MANUFACTURE, OUT WIT, OUTPLAY,
OUT THINK EVERYONE.
SO I'M EVERYWHERE PROUD OF YOU
AND CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU, R.C.
>> MICHAEL.
ON DAY 19, WAS THERE SOMETHING
THAT YOU MAYBE SHOULD HAVE TOLD
ME?
>> ON DAY 19, PENNER WAS GOING
HOME.
I HAD NO IDEA YOU WERE GOING
>> YOU DIDN'T KNOW MY NAME WAS
BEING WRITTEN DOWN?
>> NO, I KNEW PENNER WAS GOING
AND THAT'S WHAT I KNEW AND I
THOUGHT IT WAS A COMPLETE
MINDSIDE AND THAT'S THE WAY THEY
VOTED.
I WOULD NEVER HAVE WANTED TO GET
RID OF YOU.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
CONGRATULATIONS AGAIN.
>> Jeff: THANKS, R.C.
MALCOLM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HI, GUYS.
I DIDN'T HAVE QUESTIONS UNTIL
THIS THING STARTED, BUT LISA
CAME OUT AND GAVE HER OPENING
SPEECH SHE WAS SWINGING FOR THE
FENCES.
I DIDN'T THINK SHE HAD IT IN HER
BUT IT WAS EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED
TO HEAR FROM HER, AND FOR THE
FIRST TIME I REALLY CONSIDERED
WRITING YOUR NAME DOWN TONIGHT.
DENISE YOU NEEDED-- DON'T NOD.
I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW, DON'T
NOD.
DON'T NOD.
THIS APPEASING EVERYBODY THING
HAS TO STOP.
YOU'VE BEEN DOING IT SINCE DAY
ONE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO FOR A LIVING.
YOU'RE A THERAPIST.
BUT NOW I WANT TO HEAR HOW
YOU'RE GOING TO WIN THIS GAME,
HOW YOU PLAYED BETTER AND WHY
YOU DESERVED IT MORE, AND I
DON'T WANT THIS APPEASING THING,
THIS TRYING TO PLAY NICE, TRYING
TO KEEP FRIENDS THROUGH THE
ENTIRE PROCESS.
>> HOW DID I OUTWIT OR OUTPLAYED
THESE TWO.
YOU'RE RIGHT, BEING A THERAPIST
IS WHAT I DO, AND SOME OF THAT
IS APPEASING BECAUSE THERE IS
VALUE IN THIS GAME TO PLAYING
THAT SOCIAL PIECE.
BUT THERE'S ALSO VALUE IN JUST
LISTENING AND OBSERVES TO WHAT
PEOPLE SAY.
THAT'S A PART OF WHO I AM THAT I
COULDN'T NOT BRING INTO THE
GAME.
SO IT MAY SEEM APPEASING BUT I
WAS PLAYING THE GAME EVERY STEP
OF THE WAY.
AND I'M SITTING HERE AND YOU'RE
STANDING THERE.
>> YOU GOT HUNG UP ON ONE WORD.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I ASKED AT ALL.
THE QUESTION WAS HOW DID YOU
BEAT THESE TWO?
>> BY THE STRATEGY THEY PLAYED.
BY THE STRATEGY OF BEING HERE.
I I DON'T THINK THEY PLAYED THAT
KIND OF A STRATEGIC GAME.
>> THANKS.
>> Jeff: THANKS, MALCOLM.
JEFF.
>> THERE'S NO DOUBT THAT WE ALL
SHARE A LITTLE BIT OF
BITTERNESS, SOME AT DIFFERENT
LEVELS THAN OTHERS BECAUSE WE'RE
SITTING HERE AND YOU GUYS ARE
SITTING THERE.
I'M A LITTLE BITTER, TOO, BUT I
CAN HANDLE IT REALLY WELL.
SKUPIN, I'VE LEARNED THROUGHOUT
MY LIFE AND CAREER THAT THERE
ARE THREE KINDS OF PEOPLE.
PEOPLE THAT MAKE THINGS HAPPEN.
PEOPLE THAT WATCH THINGS HAPPEN.
AND PEOPLE THAT WONDER WHAT THE
HELL JUST HAPPENED.
( LAUGHTER ).
WHICH ONE ARE YOU?
GIVE ME SOME EXAMPLES IN THE
GAME OF WHICH ONE YOU ARE.
>> I WOULD DEFINITELY SAY MAKE
THINGS HAPPEN.
I MEAN, ONE OF MY FAMILY MOTOS
IS ARE YOU GOING TO WATCH THE
NEWS TODAY OR MAKE THE NEWS?
AND ONE OF THE THINGS THEY THINK
WAS HUGE HERE IS MY NECK WAS
CHOPPING BLOCK EVERY SINGLE DAY.
WHEN I LOOK AT LISA AND DENISE'S
GAME, I NEVER HEARD DENISE'S
GRAHAM NAMEBROUGHT UP.
WHEN MY NAME CAME UP, I HAD TO
SHIFT OR CREATE OR TRY AND DO
THINGS AND MY NAME CAME UP EVERY
SINGLE TIME UNTIL PENNER LEFT.
>> LISA, GIVE ME A REASON WHY,
MAYBE SOME EXAMPLES OF HOW YOU
DIDN'T PLAY IN THE MIDDLE, HOW
YOU DID FLOAT ALONG LIKE DENISE
THAT SEPARATES THE TWO OF YOU?
>> I CAN'T EVEN RECALL A TIME I
FLOATED IN THE MIDDLE.
I MAYBE SHOULD HAVE FLOATED IN
THE MIDDLE BECAUSE I WAS PRETTY
WIDE OPEN THE WHOLE TIME.
I WAS THE FIRST ONE TO MAKE A
MAJOR MOVE WHEN I FOUND OUT
MALCOLM HAD THE IDOL AND I WENT
TO PETE AND SAID THIS IS TIME TO
BLINDSIDE HIM.
WE HAD IT ALL PLANNED AND IN THE
LAST 15 MINUTES IT BLEW UP.
PETE HAD A PLAN B.
AND THAT WAS TO SEND YOU HOME,
WHICH STILL WAS GOOD, BECAUSE IT
WOULD KEEP OUR TANDANG NUMBERS--
>> THAT'S FINE ON THAT.
BUT I THINK THAT PROVES MY
EXAMPLE HERE.
YOU TRIED TO MAKE SOMETHING
HAPPEN.
YOU COULDN'T MAKE IT HAPPEN, SO
YOU JUST AGREED WITH EVERYBODY
ELSE, WHICH MEANS YOU JUST
FLOATED BY.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE AT ALL.
I AGREED BECAUSE IT WAS STILL,
ALONG WITH MY PLAN, WHICH WAS
KEEP TANDANG NUMBERS STRONG.
SO YOU WERE ON KALABAW, SO THAT
WAS A GREAT PLAN, AND I PLAYED
IT HARD FROM HERE.
I SAID WE'VE GOT PLAN B, GIETZ.
GO WITH PLAN B.
THAT'S NOT FLOATING IN THE
MIDDLE STANDING UP HERE AND
SAYING WE'VE GOT PLAN B, LET'S
GO WITH PLAN B.
THAT'S PRETTY VOCAL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ABI, YOU'RE UP.
>> HELLO, GUYS.
>> HI.
>> I WAS CALLED TO BE THE MOST
UNLIKABLE PERSON IN THE TRIBE BY
THE THREE OF YOU.
7 MY HEART'S BROKEN.
LISA, WHY DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DESERVING OF A MILLION DOLLARS?
WHY DO YOU THINK I SHOULD WRITE
DOWN YOUR NAME BECAUSE I REALLY
DON'T KNOW WHO I'M GOING TO VOTE
FOR TONIGHT.
>> I BELIEVE I'M DESERVING OF
YOUR VOTE BECAUSIST ABSOLUTELY
TRUE TO THE END WITH THIS
ALLIANCE, AND PLANNED TO GO ALL
THE WAY THE FINAL FOUR WITH THAT
ALLIANCE.
UNTIL IT DISINTEGRATED.
AND IF THAT HAD WORKED, YOU AND
ARTIS AND PETER AND I WOULD BE
SITTING IN THE FINAL FOUR.
THAT'S WHY I BELIEVE I DESERVE
YOUR VOTE.
>> MICHAEL, WHY DO YOU THINK I
SHOULD GIVE YOU A MILLION
DOLLARS TONIGHT OR DO YOU EVEN
CARE THEY WOULD WRITE YOUR NAME
DOWN OR NOT?
>> I BELIEVE THAT I DESERVE YOUR
VOTE BECAUSE WHAT THIS GAME IS
ABOUT, IT'S ABOUT OUTWIT,
OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
AND I BELIEVE IF YOU LOOK AT
THOSE THREE PRINCIPLES, THERE'S
NOBODY SITTING UP HERE THAT DID
THAT REMOTELY EVEN CLOSE TO WHAT
I DID IN THIS GAME.
>> BUT I DON'T BELIEVE ONE OF
THE CORE VALUES OF THE GAME IS
OUT-DISRESPECT.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT IS,
EITHER.
>> THANK YOU.
DENISE, YOU MADE VERY CLEAR THAT
YOU DIDN'T DNOT RESPECT MY GAME,
THAT I WAS AN UNLIKABLE PERSON,
BEING THE MOST UNLIKABLE PERSON
IS NOT THE LABEL THAT I WANTED
TO LEAVE HERE WITH.
I WAS DEMORALIZED.
I WAS MADE TO LOOK THIS LITTLE.
>> HINDSIGHT IS 20-20.
AND AS MUCH AS THERE MAY BE MANY
SENTIMENTS IN WHAT I SAID, THAT
I STILL STAND BEHIND, THERE MAY
HAVE BEEN A DIFFERENT WAY FOR ME
TO HANDLE IT.
AND I DO APOLOGIZE.
IF YOU WERE TRULY TRAUMATIZE BY
THAT, IF YOU WERE TRULY
DEMORALIZED BY THAT, I DO
APOLOGIZE.
BECAUSE THAT'S NOT MY ATTENTION.
BUT WHEN WE PRESENT OUR
STRATEGIES, JUST DIDN'T MESH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: THANKS, ABI.
PENNER.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S END THIS
THING.
GUYS, HI.
CONGRATULATIONS.
OBVIOUSLY, WE ALL WISH WE WERE
SITTING THERE.
AS JEFF SAYS, THERE IS SOME
VESTIGE OF FURY?
OF COURSE THERE IS.
HOW CAN THERE HELP BUT BE.
WE'VE ALL GIVEN OUR HEARTS AND
SOULS TO THIS GAME, SOME OF US A
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF HEART AND
SOUL.
AND TO SEE ANYONE BUT OURSELVES
SITTING THERE LOOKING AT ANYONE
ELSE IS PAINFUL.
THAT SAID, YOU HAVE MY HEART
FELT CONGRATULATIONS.
I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON TONIGHT
IS HARD.
SMART PEOPLE ASKING TOUGH
QUESTIONS.
I WILL HOPE TO CONTINUE THAT
TRADITION.
( LAUGHTER )
DENISE, WE'VE HAD A LOT OF TIME
TOGETHER.
I'M A LITTLE CONFUSED BY SOME OF
WHAT YOU SAID TONIGHT, APPEASING
IS WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU SHARED WITH ME ONCE THAT THE
ONE THING THAT YOU WERE SORT OF
AFRAID OF BEING SEEN AS WAS A
BITCH.
YOU CAN REST ASSURED THAT YOU
HAVE NOW SHOWN THE WORLD THAT
SIDE.
SKUPIN, YOU'RE SITTING HERE
TELLING US HOW YOUR NAME KEPT
COMING UP AND HOW YOU WERE
THREATENED ALL THE TIME.
I DON'T THINK YOUR NAME-- AND
YOU GUYS WILL CORRECT ME IF I'M
WRONG EYE DON'T THINK YOUR NAME
HAS BEEN WRITTEN DOWN ONE TIME
IN THIS ENTIRE GAME.
I HAVE THE PROUD DISTINCTION OF
HAVING MY NAME WRITTEN DOWN I
BELIEVE 15 TIMES.
( LAUGHTER ).
WHICH MAY BE A RECORD-- NO, I
THINK PHILLIP SHEPARD HAS MORE
TIMES, BUT I MAY HAVE CLOSE TO A
RECORD, 15 TIMES MY NAME IS
WRITTEN DOWN.
SO I KNOW THAT YOU'RE SITTING
HERE SAYING THAT THERE WAS THIS
BIG TARGET ON YOUR BACK, BUT
HOWEVER YOU SCRAMBLED OR DISSEM
BELD, BACKSTABBED AND
FLIP-FLOPPED, YOU WERE ABLE TO
AVOID HAVING YOUR NAME WRITTEN
DOWN EVEN ONCE.
YOU MAY FIND THAT YOU HAVE A
PERFECT RECORD, EVEN AFTER
TONIGHT.
LISA, MY FRIEND, WE GOT CLOSE
OUT HERE.
WE BOTH KNOW THAT WE DID.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SHARE WITH
EVERYBODY OR SHALL I?
>> EITHER ONE.
I'LL BE HAPPY TO BECAUSE I-- I
MEAN, I DON'T--
>> NO, NO, I DON'T WANT TO SHAME
YOU, SUMMER.
>> IT'S NOT A SHAME.
>> NO, NO, OF COURSE NOT.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD.
>> YEAH.
>> LEA WAS A TELEVISION STAR.
SHE SPENT NINE YEARS ON THE
TELEVISION PROGRAM "THE FACTS OF
LIFE."
FROM THE AGE OF 12 TO THE AGE OF
21, SHE WAS AMERICA'S
SWEETHEART-- STILL MAY BE.
YOU GUYS DESERVE TO KNOW THAT
WHEN YOU VOTE OR DON'T VOTE FOR
HER THAT SHE HAS KEPT THAT FROM
ALL OF YOU, AND I KEPT YOUR
SECRET SAFE UNTIL NOW.
>> CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
>> ANYTHING YOU WANT?
>> DID YOU REVEAL TO ANY OF US
WHAT YOU DID AS A TEENAGER, WHAT
JOB YOU HAD AS A TEENAGER, LIKE
25 YEARS AGO?
OR DID YOU TALK MORE ABOUT WHO
YOU ARE NOW, WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
DOING, AND WHAT YOU BRING TO THE
GAME NOW?
>> I DIDN'T TALK ABOUT WHEN I
WENT TO THE BATHROOM 16 DAYS--
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS I DIDN'T
TALK ABOUT, EITHER.
MY LIFE, WOULD YOU REALLY LIKE
TO HEAR NOW?
SHOULD WE TAKE THE TIME AND I
CAN TALK ABOUT WHAT DIWHEN I WAS
12 TO 21.
IF YOU GUYS ARE INTERESTED, I
DON'T THINK IT'S GOING TO AFFECT
THE OUTCOME TONIGHT.
MAYBE LATER I'LL TELL YOU ALL
ABOUT IT.
I THINK THAT ONE OF YOU HAS
RIDDEN THE OTHER TWO IN HERE.
LIKE OXEN.
YOU HAVE BEEN YOKED TO A CART
AND HAVE BEEN RIDDEN IN, AND NOW
YOU WILL BE LED TO THE
SLAUGHTER.
AND YOU HEAR THE CHEERING.
YOU THINK THE MILLION DOLLARS IS
YOURS.
ONE OF YOU IS RIGHT.
ONE OF OF YOU IS STANDING IN THE
CHARIOT.
AND THE OTHER TWO ARE ACTUALLY
JUST THE OXIEN LISTENING TO THE
CROWD CHEERING THE OTHER PERSON.
I'M DONE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY.
A VERY LIVELY FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
HOPEFULLY, YOU GATHERED THE
INFORMATION YOU NEED TO NOW MAKE
A VERY BIG DECISION.
WHICH ONE OF THESE THREE-- LISA,
SKUPIN, OR DENISE-- DO YOU THINK
MOST DESERVES TO WIN THIS GAME
AND THE MILLION DOLLARS THAT
GOES ALONG WITH IT?
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A MOMENT
TO GATHER YOUR THOUGHTS.
WE'LL COME BACK AND WE WILL
VOTE.
LISA, SKUPIN, DENISE.
YOU HAD YOUR CHANCE TO ADDRESS
THE JURY.
THE JURY HAS HAD THEIR CHANCE TO
ADDRESS YOU.
WE NOW GET TO THE VOTE.
JURY, YOU ARE VOTING FOR A
WINNER.
THE PERSON'S NAME WHO YOU WRITE
DOWN YOU THINK IS MOST DESERVING
OF WINNING THIS GAME AND THE
MILLION DOLLARS THAT GOES WITH
IT.
39 DAYS OF "SURVIVOR" CAN TAKE A
TREMENDOUS TOLL ON A PERSON.
FOR ONE OF YOU, IT'S ABOUT TO BE
WORTH IT.
FOR THE LAST TIME, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
JEFF, YOU'RE UP.
>> THE MINUTE I GOT ON THE RAFT
I WANTED YOU GONE BECAUSE I KNEW
WHAT A THREAT YOU WERE.
SO YOU CERTAINLY DESERVE THIS
VOTE.
>> YOU PLAYED A PRETTY FLAWLESS
GAME.
MY CONGRATULATIONS TO YOU.
IT HURTS, BUT DID YOU GREAT.
'RE
>> I HOPE OTHER PEOPLE RECOGNIZE
THE TYPE OF GAME YOU PLAYED OUT
HERE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO GET THE
VOTES.
THANK YOU FOR A GREAT SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR."
I WILL SEE EVERYBODY BACK IN THE
STATES FOR THE READING OF THE
VOTES.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: THANK YOU!
THANK YOU.
EVERYBODY HAVE A SEAT.
THANK YOU FOR THAT NICE WELCOME.
OKAY.
WE ARE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES, AND
TONIGHT I WILL READ THE VOTES,
AND THERE LAIB WINNER OF
"SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES."
BUT BEFORE WE GET TO THAT, WE'RE
GOING TO TAKE A MOMENT OF
SILENCE FOR THE VICTIMS AND THE
FAMILIES OF THE TRAGEDY THAT
OCCURRED ON FRIDAY IN NEWTOWN,
CONNECTICUT.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO READ THE VOTES.
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS )
LISA, SKUPIN, DENISE.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST VOTE, LISA.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
DENISE
ONE VOTE LISA, ONE VOTE DENISE.
SKUPIN.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
ONE VOTE LISA, ONE VOTE SKUPIN,
ONE VOTE DENISE.
DENISE.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
TWO VOTES DENISE, ONE VOTE LISA,
ONE VOTE SKUPIN.
DENISE.
( APPLAUSE )
THREE VOTES DENISE, ONE VOTE
LISA, ONE VOTE SKUPIN.
THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR:
PHILIPPINES," DENISE.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
GO HUG YOUR FAMILY.
>> Jeff: THE LIVE REUNION SHOW
IS NEXT.