>> PREVIOUSLY ON "SURVIVOR". . .
>> WITH JEFF LEADING THE CHARGE
AGAINST VETERANS, A LONG HUNT
FOR THE IDOL PAID OFF.
>> ON THE TOP ON THE RIGHT, A
LITTLE WOODEN BULL.
THE IDEA TOLL WAS RIGHT UNDER
YOUR NOSE.
I HAVE THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> LISA, THE FORMER FACTS OF
LIFE STAR CONTINUED TO HIDE
OTHER IDENTITY AND WAS LOOKING
LIKE THE FIRST TO GO.
>> IT'S HARD BEING ON THE
OUTSIDE.
MAYBE I'M NOT ABLE TO PLAY THIS
>> WHEN R.C. DISCOVERED THE
CLUES TO THE HIDDEN IDOL, SHE
DECIDED TO SHARE IT WITH HER
CLOSEST ALLY.
BUT RC FOUND EVERY CLUE DOESN'T
ALWAYS LEAD TO.
>> I AM YOUR FRIEND.
>> THIS MEANS YOU'RD.
>> AFTER THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
AN INTENSE BATTLE BETWEEN THREE
TRIBES.
GAVE MATT ZING THEIR SECOND LEAD
IN A ROW.
>> THEY SHOULDN'T BEAT US AND
THEY HAVE TWICE.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE THESE FOLKS
HAVEN'T DECIDED THEY CAN DO
THIS.
>> AT CAMP, RUSS AND HE WILL
ROSSI GOT TO ANGIE.
ANGIE AND MALCOMB WANTED ROCKY
TO GO.
>> ROXIE IS GOING HOME.
>> LEAVING DENISE STUCK IN THE
MIDDLE.
>> I HAVE GOT TO THINK
LONG-TERM.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNSEL, ROXIE
CONTINUED HER CASE.
>> TO PAIR IN GAME IS
DANGEROUS.
GOOD LUCK TO THE REST OF YOU IF
YOU CHOOSE HER OVER ME.
>> IN THE END DENISE SIDED WITH
HER ALLY, MALCOMB.
>> ROXIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> 16 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> THAT WAS FUN.
>> IT'S INTERESTING.
>> IT WAS ALL UNNECESSARY.
>> WELL, THAT'S THE GAME.
>> STARTING WITH TRIBAL COUNSEL
AND ROXIE JUST KIND OF EXPLODED.
SHE WANTED TO GO OUT WITH A
BANG, I THINK, SO HER STRATEGY
WAS JUST TO THROW ME AND MALCOLM
UNDER THE BECAUSE BECAUSE THAT'S
THE ONLY THING SHE COULD EVEN
SAY.
>> IT'S JUST PART OF THE GAME.
SHE HAS TO POINT OUT ANOTHER
THREAT THAT IS NOT HERS.
>> WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR NOW AND
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF THEM TRUST
ME AND I TRUST ALL OF THEM AND
THEY KNOW ME AND MALCOMB ARE
NOTHING BUT FRIENDS.
THEY ALL KNOW THAT.
>> BAD NEWS IS WE HAD TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNSEL AGAIN AND THERE'S
ONLY FOUR OF US.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THERE'S ONLY
FOUR OF US SO LET'S MAKE THIS
HAPPEN.
ROXIE WAS ABSOLUTELY RIGHT
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
THAT ALLIANCE BETWEEN MALCOMB
AND ANGIE REAL AND I THINK IT
WAS PRETTY TIGHT.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THAT'S
TWO VOTES.
SO ALL THEY NEED IS ONE MORE.
IF SHE HITCHES TO THE YOUNG ONES
T
HEN I'M DEAD.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> I JUST NEED TO CHILL TODAY.
>> WOULDN'T YOU FEEL BETTER IF
YOU HAD THE IDOL.
>> I WANT TO GET IT OVER AND
DONE WITH AND PUT AWAY AND
THAT'S IT.
>> I KNOW.
BUT I NEED TO GET MYSELF 100%.
>> I'M CONCERNED BECAUSE I'M IN
TROUBLE BECAUSE I HAVE ANY KNEE
INJURED.
I TWISTED MY KNEE TWICE SINCE I
HAVE BEEN HERE.
AND I'M NOT TRUSTING RC WITH
THAT CLUE FOR THE IDOL ANYMORE.
>> YOU'RE NOT A LIABILITY.
>> I TRUST MYSELF MORE THAN
ANYBODY HERE SO I'M GOING WITH
THAT AND HOPE MY LEG GETS
BETTER.
>> ABI, YOU'RE MISSING MY POINT.
>> JUST BE FORWARD.
>> YOOM.
I'M SAYING YOU'RE NOT A
LIABILITY.
>> YOU SAID THAT 10 TIMES BUT
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> YOU KNOW AND HE ABI CLICKED
FROM DAY ONE AND BUILT AN
ALLIANCE TOGETHER AND I TRUST
HER.
I'M 100% WITH HER BUS SHE'S A
LITTLE MORE HESITANT AND HER
PAIR I DIDN'TA, I THINK, IS
GETTING THE BEST OF HER RIGHT
NOW.
>> JUST LIKE YOU DON'T THINK WE
CAN GET THE IDOL --
>> LET ME FINISH.
>> GO GO AHEAD.
>> I'M SAYING IT'S POINTLESS.
>> ABI, STOP IT.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> IF YOU WANT TO FINISH.
>> PLEASE STOP.
>> I'M HERE TO LISTEN TO YOU.
>> JUST STOP.
>> STOP FIGHTING.
>> I'M NOT FIGHTING.
>> I'M NOT FIGHTING WITH YOU.
I'M NOT WASTING MY TIME.
>> ABI DEFINITELY GOT A LITTLE
HARD-CORE WITH OUR CONVERSATION.
WE GAVE EACH OTHER OUR WORD.
OUR WORD IS OUR BOND.
I FEEL I SHARED THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL WITH HER AND THAT
SHOULD PROVE I TRUST HER MORE
THAN ANYONE ELSE IN THE GAME.
>> IT'S LIKE YOU JUST BIT MY
HEAD OFF.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> WE FOUND THE CLUE INSIDE THE
RICE, YOU KNOW.
IT WAS RIGHT THERE.
AND THE CLUE FOR THE IMMUNITY
IDOL WAS RIGHT UNDER YOUR NOSE.
>> WE HAVE AN ALLIANCE OF MIKE,
RC, PETER AND US.
PETER HAS BEEN A BIT MORE
GENUINE WITH ME.
>> I SHARED THE NEWS WITH PETER,
SO WE HAVE THE CLUE AND WE WANT
TO FIND IT BEFORE RC DOES.
>> HAVE YOU CHECKED IN THE BAG
OF RICE ALL THE WAY AT THE
BOTTOM.
>> YEAH, WE STUCK OUR HANDS ALL
IN IT.
>> I DON'T LIKE STEPPING INTO
THINGS UNTIL I KNOW WHAT IS
GOING ON.
>> YOU'RE LUCKY I TRUST YOU
BECAUSE NOW I DON'T TRUST RC.
>> I LOOK LIKE I DON'T PAY
ATTENTION BUT I'M PAYING
ATTENTION TO EVERYTHING AROUND
ME.
IT'S LIKE I'M ON SURVEILLANCE
BECAUSE I'M SITTING THERE AND
LISTENING AND THEN I KNOW WHAT
MOVES TO ME.
>> SO HOW MUCH DO YOU VALUE
STAYING IN THE GAME?
>> I WANT TO STAY IN THE GAME
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
>> OK.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW -- I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU KNOW, BUT THEY WANT TO
GET RID OF YOU FIRST, RIGHT?
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
>> WELL, I GUESS, YES.
>> BUT I CAN MAKE STUFF HAPPEN
WHERE YOU DON'T GO HOME.
BUT WE MIGHT HAVE TO -- FOR YOU
TO STAY IN, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO GET RID OF SOMEBODY.
>> I FEEL LIKE AN ALLIANCE IS
ONLY AS STRONG AS THE DAY IT IS
MADE.
THEY WANT TO PUT LISA ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK TO GET RID OF HER
FIRST.
I LIKE LISA.
I DON'T SEE ANY PROBLEM WITH HER
AND I SEE SOMEBODY LATER IN THE
GAME THAT I CAN GET RID OF.
>> WOULD YOU BE OK IF WE HAD TO
GET RID OF MIKE?
HE IS GOING TO BE A REAL PROBLEM
AT THE END AND THE LAST PEOPLE
WE HAVE, THE HARDER IT'S GOING
TO BE.
>> SO PETER IS WANTING TO
BLINDSIDE MIKE.
>> AND I WOULD PREFER TO
BLINDSIDE RC BUT PETER IS THE
ONE THAT IS CALLING IT SO I NEED
TO LAY LOW AND GO WITH HIM.
JUST TELL ME WHAT TO DO AND I
WILL FOLLOW YOUR LEAD.
>> ALL I NEED FOR YOU IS WHEN I
TELL YOU TO VOTE FOR SOMEBODY TO
VOTE.
>> OK.
>> THEN WE HAVE THREE VOTES, ME,
YOU AND ABI AND HE IS GONE.
>> WOW.
>> THE BEST ANALOGY AND I'M NOT
EVEN A CARD PLAYER, IS THAT JEFF
FEELS LIKE I'M DEALT A NEW HAND
EVERY DAY, AND EVERY DAY I HAVE
TO PLAY THE HAND THAT I HAVE.
YOU'RE UP AND DOWN AND UP AND
DOWN.
SO TODAY, I'M UP BUT I'M
CAUTIOUSLY UP.
>> MIKE, RC, AND THEN TAKE IT
FROM THERE.
>>
>> MY ASS HURTS.
AND I DON'T KNOW IT UNTIL I LIE
BACK DOWN.
>> DID YOU TAKE THIS SPOT?
>> NO.
THAT WAS LIKE A PATTERN THING.
>> A LITTLE RICE PATTERN THING?
>> WHERE DID THAT GO?
>> DANA AND I ENDED UP LOOKING
AT THE RICE BOX AND ON TOP OF
THE LID THERE WAS AN EMBLEM THAT
WAS NAILED TO THE TOP OF THE
RICE BOX.
WE NOTICED THAT PIECE IS GONE
NOW.
YOU KNOW THAT THING THAT WAS ON
TOP OF THE RICE LID AIN'T THERE
ANYMORE.
>> IT MIGHT BE THE IDOL.
>> THAT LITTLE DESIGN PIECE THAT
WAS STUCK ON THERE, THAT PIECE,
I BUT YOU HE HAS IT.
>> YOU'RE STARING AT THAT THING
THE WHOLE TIME.
>> I'M PISSED OFF AND NOT AT
JONATHAN.
I GIVE HIM PROPS.
IT WAS IN OUR FACE.
WE TOUCHED IT.
WE LOOKED AT IT.
WE WEREN'T EVEN CURIOUS ABOUT
IT.
AND THAT'S A PURE VETERAN MOVE.
>> WE HAVE A CHALLENGE AND WE
LOSE, WE WILL PLAY IT LIKE WE
HAVE NO CLUE ABOUT IT.
>> PEOPLE WHO WIN THE IDOL WILL
GET VOTED OUT.
>> EASY.
HE HAS NO CLUE.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY PLANS TO
CONFRONT JONATHAN RIGHT NOW
ABOUT THE IDOL.
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO PULL A
BLINDSIDE WHERE WE CAN GET
JONATHAN OFF OF THE ISLAND'S
POCKET.
ABOVE EVERYTHING I'M TICKED THAT
I LET THE IDOL GO RIGHT BETWEEN
MY EYES.
>> I LOOKED AT IT.
IT WAS RIGHT -- IT WAS RIGHT IN
OUR FACE.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE KIDDING ME.
>> NOPE.
>> NO FREAKING WAY!
>> WOKE UP THIS MORNING, DENISE
LOOKS DOWN THE BEACH AND SEES
OUR RAFT IS GONE.
WE THOUGHT WE HAD IT ABOVE THE
TIDE LINE BUT IT'S JUST GONE.
LITTLE BIT OF A MORALE DOWNER.
THAT COULD COME BACK TO HAUNT
US.
>>
>> LAST NIGHT THERE WAS NO
CUDDLING WHATSOEVER.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> THEY HAVE NO IDEA.
>> TRIBE OF SIX IS ALREADY DOWN
TO FOUR.
AND ME AND DENISE HAVE BEEN
TIGHT FROM THE BEGINNING,,.
IF WE GO BACK TO TRIBAL IT WILL
COME DOWN TO ANGIE OR RUSSELL
BUT RIGHT NOW THERE'S NO CLEAR
CUT NEXT CHOICE TO GO HOME.
>> WE WILL MAKE THE DECISION
WHEN IT COMES TIME.
NO SURVEY.
>> EXACTLY.
I REALLY LIKE THAT.
I'M FINE, MALCOMB IN THE MIDDLE.
>> THERE WAS SUCH A FOCUS ON
MALCOMB AND ANGIE, A AS COUPLE
AT TRIBAL COUNSELING BUT I'M
STILL HOLDING THAT TRUST MALCOMB
AND I WHEN THE TIME COMES HE
WILL CUT ANGE.
BECAUSE IT'S A NUMBERS GAME I
FEEL STRONGER HAVING RUSSELL
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO WIN A
CHALLENGE.
>> IT'S NICE TO KNOW WE'RE COOL.
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE DECISIONS.
>> NOT ON THIS ONE.
>> ARE YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> JEFF: FIRST THING'S FIRST.
I TAKE BACK THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
DIVE DOWN TO RELEASE PUZZLE
WHEELS ATTACHED TO A LINE.
ONCE YOU HAVE ONE, YOU WILL
BRING IT UP AND THE NEXT PERSON
GUESS.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL EIGHT WHEELS
YOU USE THOSE WHEELS TO SOLVE A
WORD PUZZLE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO GET IT
RIGHT, WIN IMMUNITY, ARE SAFE
FROM THE VOTE.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNSEL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE THIRD
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
MATSING YOU HAVE BEEN TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL TWO TIMES IN A ROW, YOU
DO NOT WANT TO GO AGAIN.
IN ADDITION YOU ARE ONCE AGAIN
PLAYING FOR REWARD.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH, IT'S A
MASSIVE FISHING KIT.
YOU HAVE LINE, BAIT, A NET, YOU
HAVE A CANOE WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP AND A COUPLE OF
PADDLES.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH, A
SMALLER FISHING KIT, NOT QUITE
AS BIG BUT STILL PRETTY NICE.
YOU'RE SITTING TWO PEOPLE OUT.
>> KATIE AND DAWSON.
>> TANDANG YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
MEMBERS.
>> I TWISTED MY KNEE TWICE SO --
>> ABI IS ONE.
>> I'M THE OTHER.
>> LISA IS THE OTHER.
ABI AND LISA SITTING OUT TORE
TANDANG.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I WILL GIVE YOU
A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
AND WE WILL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
[CHEERING]
>> DANA FIRST UP.
ONE FOR TANDANG.
ANGIE IS STRUGGLING.
AT FIRST PUZZLE PIECES ONLY TWO
FEET DEEP.
DANA IS BACK FOR KALABAW.
JEFF NOW HEADED BACK.
ANGIE HAS THE FIRST PUZZLE
PIECE.
SHE'S SWIMMING IT BACK FORMAT
SING.
QUICK WORK OF IT FOR KALABAW.
JEFF IS FAST WITH THE SECOND
WATER PIECE.
RUSSELL NOW IN THE WATER FORMAT
SING.
PETE NOW BACK WITH THE SECOND
PUZZLE PIECE FOR TANDANG.
THERE
RUSSELL WITH THE SECOND PUZZLE
PIECE.
THERE ARE 8 TOTAL.
CARTER IN THE WATER FOR KALABAW.
RUSSELL TRYING TO GET UP AND
LOSING SOME TIME.
>> RC IN THE WATER FOR TANDANG.
>> BLEEDING FROM THE FACE.
RUSSELL FINALLY UP.
DENISE IN THE WATER.
BACK WITH THE FOURTH PIECE FOR
KALABAW.
DANA BACK IN THE WATER.
KALABAW WITH A BIG LEAD.
DENISE, INCREDIBLY FAST.
>> GO DANA!
>> RC GOING AGAIN NOW.
DENISE BACK WITH THE THIRD PIECE
FORMAT SING IN RECORD TIME.
>> HERE COMES DANA WITH THAT
FIFTH PUZZLE PIECE FOR KALABAW.
JEFF BACK IN THE WATER FOR
KALABAW.
RC HAS GOT ENTWO PIECES IN A ROW
FOR HER TRIBE.
GOING BACK FOR A THIRD.
>> MALCOMB BACK WITH THE FOURTH
PIECE.
RUSSELL BACK IN THE WATER AFTER
STRUGGLING HIS FIRST TIME OUT.
COMING BACK WITH THE 6th
PIECE.
TWO PIECES LEFT FOR KALABAW.
RC COMING BACK WITH HER THIRD
PIECE.
TANDANG WITH TWO PIECES LEFT.
EACH PIECE GETS DEEPER AND IT
GETS TOUGHER AND THE PRESSURE
GETS STRONGER.
RUSSELL COMES BACK, EMPTY HANDED
FORMAT SING AND THAT IS GOING TO
COST HIM A LOT OF TIME.
MICHAEL BLEEDING AND BACK IN THE
WATER.
>> RUSSELL CAN'T GET UP THE
LADDER.
MATSING HAS FOUR PIECES TO GO.
MATSING JUST LOT A LOT OF TIME
WHEN RUSSELL WENT OUT AND CAME
BACK WITHOUT A PIECE.
DENISE IS A MACHINE, PICKING UP
A LOT OF TIME.
CARTER FOR THAT LAST PIECE,
SKUPIN BACK WITH A PIECE FOR
TANDANG.
HERE GOES MALCOMB: KALABAW WITH
THEIR LAST PIECE.
HERE COMES CARTER.
THEY CAN START WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLE.
MALCOMB BACK WITH THE 6th
PIECE.
RC BACK WITH THE 8th PIECE FOR
TANDANG.
DENISE BACK IN THE WATER FOR A
THIRD TIME.
TANDANG STARTS WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
TANDANG ONCE AGAIN IS DEAD LAST.
DENISE WITH THE 7th PIECE.
MALCOMB OUT FOR THE FINAL PIECE
FORMAT SING.
REMEMBER YOU'RE SOLVING IT FROM
THIS SIDE.
THERE YOU GO.
MALCOMB BACK WITH THAT 8th AND
FINAL PIECE.
HE IS UP.
NOW GO.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLE.
YOU NEED TO PICK IT UP MATSING.
TANDANG STILL TRYING DIFFERENT
COMBINATIONS.
MATSING IS CATCHING UP.
THEY'RE BACK IN THIS.
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE IN
THIS GAME TOMORROW YOU NEED TO
NOT BE LAST TODAY.
>> KALABAW THINKS THEY HAVE IT
AND THEY DO!
KALABAW FINISHES!
>> TANDANG THINKS THEY HAVE IT
AND THEY DO.
TREASURE IS THE WORD.
TANDANG WINS IMMUNITY, MATSING,
WINLESS HEADED TO TRIBE COUNCIL
FOR THE THIRD STRAIGHT TIME.
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> HOW ABOUT ONCE AGAIN, GOOD
WORK.
TANDANG NICE EFFORT.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR YOU GUYS.
KALABAW IN ADDITION TO IMMUNITY,
A HUGE FISHING KIT WILL BE
WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
TANDANG, A SMALLER BUT STILL
EFFECTIVE FISHING KIT WILL BE
WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
MATSING FOR THE THIRD STRAIGHT
WEEK I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNSEL WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT OF YOUR TRIBE.
>> RUSSELL STRUGGLED IN
CHALLENGE FOR THE FIRST TIME.
HE HAD A HARD TIME GETTING UP
THE LADDER AND THEN THE SECOND
TIME RUSSELL JUST KIND OF GAVE
UP.
AND THAT'S THE THING -- YOU KNOW
ME MIGHT BE BIG AND HE MIGHT BE
STRONG BUT HE IS THE WEAK LINK.
>> GUYS THAT WAS ANOTHER
FANTASTIC VICTORY.
>> HIGH 5.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THE CHALLENGE WAS AWESOME.
WE TOOK FIRST PLACE IN IT AND IT
FELT GOOD TO WHICH SOME FISHING
STUFF.
WE ARE ALWAYS WANTING TO EAT.
I THINK THAT WORKS OUT.
WE'RE A HUNGRY TRIBE.
>> LET'S GET SOME HYDRATION AND
FIGURE OUT HOW WE'RE GOING TO DO
THIS.
>> THE CHALLENGE WAS FANTASTIC.
BUT AS WE'RE COME BACK.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
I BELIEVE JEFF KNOWS I'M AN
EXPERIENCED PLAYER.
HE 1 VERY WARY OF ME.
BUT I WANT HIM TO BE ON MY SIDE
AND I WANT HIM TO TRUST ME.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT YOU TRUST
ME AND YOU THINK I HAVE THE
ISLAND.
I DO HAVE THE ISLAND.
>> THAT WAS ALL UNDER OUR NOSES
FOR A WHILE.
>> I HAVE THE IDOL.
NOW WE'RE SEPARATED AND I HOPE
WE CAN COME BACK TOGETHER.
>> OBVIOUSLY YOU WANT TO GET
AHEAD IN THE GAME AND I DO TOO.
IF IT MEANS I GOT TO RIDE IN
YOUR BOAT YOU HAVE POWER AND
KNOWLEDGE, I WILL RIDE IN YOUR
BOAT FOR A WHILE.
>> I WILL TRY TO BEFRIEND HIM A
LITTLE BIT AND FORGE A BETTER
RELATIONSHIP.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT WILL
BE BEST FOR ME.
THIS IS A ME GAME.
IT ISN'T A WE GAME.
I GUESS YOU PROVE SOME OF YOUR
LOYALTY.
>> I'M TRYING TO PROVE IT BY
LETTING YOU KNOW.
>> NOTHING WE CAN DO UNTIL --
EXACTLY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOOD DEAL.
>> AT THE END HE WANTED TO CUT A
DEAL WITH A HANDSHAKE SO I GAVE
HIM A FOUR FINGER HANDSHAKE, NOT
A FIVE-FINGER HANDSHAKE.
I'M NOT SO COMMITTED, IN MY BOOK
UNLESS IT'S A MANLY HANDSHAKE,
IT'S NOT GOING TO COUNT.
>> TANDANG?
>> TANDANG.
>> THAT WAS A TOUGH ONE.
>> AND YOU TOOK ANOTHER ONE FOR
THE TEAM ON THE FACE.
>> I HIT THE WATER AND I OPENED
MY EYES AND I COULDN'T SEE
ANYTHING.
>> SO YOU BROKE IT.
>> CAN YOU GET ANYMORE INJURIES.
>> TODAY'S CHALLENGE WAS
EXTREMELY DISAPPOINTING FOR ME.
THE POSITIVE IS THAT WE DON'T
HAVE TO TO GO TO TRIBAL COUNSEL.
WE SHOULD HAVE WON.
MIKE DECIDED TO DIVE FACE FIRST
IN THE WATER WITH THE MASK AND
THE MASK CRASH AFTER TELLING ME
NOT TO DIVE WITH THE MASK, WHO
DOVE WITH THE MASK NO PROBLEM
WHATSOEVER.
>> DOES NOBODY ELSE WANT TO GO?
>> I WILL GO.
>> I'M ABOUT FED UP WITH MIKE.
NOW HE IS IN MY SITES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ARE WE GOING CLAM DIGGING?
>> WE'RE GO TO HAVE A CLAM BAKE
TONIGHT.
>>
>> WHAS'SUP?
>> WELL, EVERYONE IS TALKING
CLAMS, I WAS GETTING RIDE ON TO
WORK, WITH YOUR BEACH UNDER YOUR
NOSE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU SHOULD BE?
HELP ME.
THEY ALL WENT OUT LOOKING FOR
CLAMS AND I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW,
IT'S GOING TO BE EITHER ME
FINDING THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
OR RC SO I TOOK THE OPPORTUNITY,
I WENT AFTER IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHERE TO LOOK
ANYMORE.
>> WE'RE TOO LATE.
RIGHT UNDER YOUR NOSE.
>> MAYBE WE'RE ON TOP OF IT.
>> WONDER IF I SHOULD TAKE THAT
SYMBOL OFF THE RICE.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I FOUND IT.
OH, MY GOSH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I FOUND IT!
>> THIS IS FREAKING AMAZING.
I KNEW WHERE IT WAS!
THE WHOLE TIME.
I KNEW IT.
>> ABI FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL RIGHT ON TOP OF THE BAG OF
RICE WHICH IS A GOOD THING
BECAUSE SHE'S MY RIGHT HAND MAN.
>> LET'S NOT BE STUPID.
>> WE KNOW WE HAVE NUMBERS.
>> OK.
SOUNDS GOOD.
>> SO I'M THINKING I COULD
DEFINITELY GET ARTIS AND LISA TO
DO WHATEVER I WANT SO IT'S GOING
TO BE EASIER TO GET RID OF MIKE
AND NEUTRALIZE RC.
>> I'M SO HAPPY I FOUND IT; I
FOUND IT.
>> I JUST WANT TO SCREAM.
IT'S JUST TRAGIC THAT I'M STUCK
OUT HERE WITH THE GOON SQUAD OF
TRIBES.
WE HAVE A GIRL WHO COULDN'T GET
A FLOAT OUT FROM UNDER TWO FEET
OF WATER.
RUSSELL BUILT LIKE AN OX AND
CAN'T CLIMB A THREE FOOT LADDER
OUT OF THE OCEAN.
NOTHING HAS GONE RIGHT.
THIS IS THE GROUP OF GOONS I GET
STUCK WITH?
IT'S LIKE -- THANK GOD FOR
DENISE.
DENISE WAS A WAR HORSE TODAY, A
LITTLE MUNCH KIN OF MUSCLE, JUST
CRANKED THEM OUT.
>> SERIOUSLY HOW MANY TIMES DID
YOU GO DOWN.
>> I DID THREE.
>> SO WE BOTH DID THREE.
>> WHAT THE HELL, SHE COULDN'T
EVEN GET THE FIRST ONE.
AND THEN RUSSELL?
COULDN'T CLIMB THE LADDER.
GRAB THE SIDE.
WE'RE GETTING HIT ONE BY ONE.
>> HEY, YOU --
>> FOR THE RECORD I NEVER SAID I
CAN'T DO THOSE.
>> I DON'T WANT MALCOMB AND
DENISE TO THINK OF ME AS A WEAK
LINK OR AS A GIRL WHO JUST GIVES
UP BECAUSE I NEVER SAID I CAN'T.
I MEAN I AM THE YOUNGEST.
I HAVE BEEN PROVING MYSELF AND I
HOPE THEY CAN SEE THAT.
>> I NEVER SAID I CAN'T.
I WOULDN'T DO THAT TO MY TEAM.
I WON'T DO IT.
I WON'T GO.
>> I KNOW.
WE KNOW YOU DID.
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE A
RIDICULOUS CHOICE TO KEEP ANGIE
AT THIS POINT BUT I DON'T KNOW
THAT I COULD GET MALCOMB TO VOTE
ANGIE AND RUSSELL, RUSSELL
COULDN'T CLIMB A LADDER.
MAYBE ME NEEDS TO GO HOME.
>> IT'S A TOUGH DECISION.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING.
>> I THINK RUSSELL.
>> YEAH.
HANG IN THERE.
>> WE LOST THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AGAIN.
AND EVERYBODY THAT IS THEIR
WEAKNESSES.
MINE SHOWED UP TODAY, DIVING
10 FEET DOWN, THAT'S JUST NOT MY
THING.
>> WELL, LORD, WHATEVER YOUR
WILL BE THY WILL BE DONE.
>> IT'S HARD TO SEE A CLEAR PATH
FORWARD.
IF THEY WANT TO MAKE A BOLD MOVE
AND GET RID OF ME BECAUSE THIS
IS THE TIME TO GET RID OF A
STRONG PLAYER, I COULD BE GONE.
>> EVEN RIGHT NOW LORD, I SAY
HALLELUIAH.
>> WHAT IS IT ABOUT THIS GAME
THAT FRIGHTENS ME SO MUCH?
LAST TIME I ALMOST DIED.
THIS TIME I THOUGHT IT WAS
DIFFERENT AND THEN WE LOSE THE
FIRST CHALLENGE AND THE SECOND
CHALLENGE AND NOW WE LOST THE
THIRD CHALLENGE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S
GOD'S PLAN FOR ME TO BE HERE FOR
JUST A SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME.
>> THANK YOU.
>> JESUS CHRIST NAME, AMEN.
>> I AM DOWN BUT I AM NOT OUT.
♪ .
>> I WOULD HAVE GONE AGAIN.
I WOULD HAVE GONE 12 BUT I WOULD
HAVE WENT AND DENISE WENT RIGHT
FOR IT BECAUSE SHE IS SUPER
FAST.
I WOULD RATHER HAVE SOMEONE DO
IT THAT IS FAST.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN'T DO IT BUT
I WANTED US TO GO AHEAD AND BE
FAST.
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE?
>> TOTALLY.
HE QUIT AND YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
QUIT.
>> HE DID QUIT.
>> TONIGHT IS HARD.
THE FIRST TWO ARE EASY.
BETWEEN RUSS AND ANGIE, IT'S A
TOSS UP FOR DIFFERENT REASONS.
ME AND RUSS HAVE NOT TALKED
STRATEGY SINCE DAY ONE.
ANGIE ON THE OTHER HAND IS -- I
WOULDN'T SAY IN MY POCKET BUT
SHE WOULD DO WHATEVER WE WANT TO
DO.
I JUST HAVE TO KEEP MYSELF
POSITIONED AS STRONG AS I
POSSIBLY CAN.
>> WE HAVE TO WIN SOMETHING.
WE CAN'T KEEP LOSING EVERYTHING.
>> I MEAN, YEAH, I SUCKED BUT
HE'S 20 YEARS OLDER THAN ME, A
HUNDRED POUNDS MORE THAN ME.
>> HE IS MORE THAN TWICE YOUR
AGE.
>> I TRUST MALCOMB AND I KNOW
DENISE AND MALCOMB WILL GET OUT
RUSSELL.
I DO FEEL BAD BECAUSE HE WANTS
THIS SO BAD AND HE WANTS TO MAKE
THE MERGE SO BAD.
>> BUT HE IS NOT DOING ANYTHING.
I MEAN HE IS GREAT AROUND CAMP.
>> TONIGHT AT CAMP I WANT TO
SHOW THEM AND SAY I'M HERE TO
WIN, I WILL DO 100%, I'M HERE TO
DO ANYTHING IT TAKES AND I WANT
TO WIN.
THAT'S MY NUMBER ONE GOAL.
>> THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO HAVE COME BEFORE ME.
MY ANCESTORS WHO HAVE DEALT WITH
THE MIDDLE PASSAGE, JIM CROW,
WHATEVER -- PEOPLE WHOSE
SHOULDERS I STAND ON HAVE
PERSEVERED, AND AT THE END OF
THE DAY, THAT'S WHERE I'M GOING
TO DRAW MY STRENGTH.
BECAUSE TO NOT CONTINUE TO FIGHT
WOULD BE TO SPIT IN THE FACE OF
ALL OF THOSE PEOPLE WHO ENDURED
SO MUCH MORE THAN I WILL EVER
ENDURE IN MY LIFE, AND
DEFINITELY IN THIS DAM GAME.
>> WELL, THE BAD NEWS IS, YOU
WILL BE DOWN TO THREE AFTER
TONIGHT.
THE GOOD NEWS IS FOR THE THREE
THAT WILL REMAIN, YOU'RE NOT
OUT.
DENISE, WHAT DID YOU SACRIFICE
TO COME OUT HERE?
>> OH, SIX WEEKS AWAY FROM MY
DAUGHTER WHO I LOVE TO DEATH AND
MY HUSBAND.
I OWN A PRIVATE PRACTICE AT HOME
SO I LOSE INCOME.
I HAVE CLIENTS THAT I HOPE ARE
OK.
IT'S HUGE.
I'M NOT WILLING TO ROLL OVER AND
JUST GIVE UP.
>> MALCOMB, HOW BIG OF A DEAL
WITH THIS FOR YOU?
>> I MEAN THE FIRST SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR" AIRED WHEN I WAS 12
YEARS OLD.
YOU'RE LAYING IN BED THINKING
HOW COOL THAT WOULD BE IF IT'S
YOU ONE DAY.
IT'S OVER A DECADE LATER AND I'M
FINALLY HERE AND IT'S GOING THIS
POORLY, I'M NOT AN EMOTIONAL GUY
IN THE SLIGHTEST BUT I WAS
BETWEEN TEARS AND SCREAMING
AFTER THE CHALLENGE TODAY, AND I
HAVE FRIENDS AND FAMILY BACK
HOME WHO ARE JUST GOING TO
ASSOCIATE ME WITH THE TRIBE THAT
KEEPS HAVING TO GO SEE YOU EVERY
TRIBAL COUNCIL: IT'S HEART
BREAKING IS THE WORD.
>> HEART BREAKING.
>> WHICH IS DIFFERENT FROM
FRUSTRATION.
>> FRUSTRATION WAS DAY THREE.
ON DAY EIGHT IT'S HEART
BREAKING.
>> SO MALCOMB WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> WE'RE PAST THE TIME OF
PLAYING NICE HOW CHALLENGES GO.
CERTAIN PEOPLE STRUGGLED TODAY.
THAT'S ON THOSE WHO KNEW WE WERE
CAPABLE OF THINGS AT THIS
CHALLENGE AND DIDN'T TAKE OVER
EARLIER.
>> I DIDN'T APPEAR YOU OR DENISE
STRUGGLE.
>> I'M NOT BEATING AROUND THE
BUSH.
ANGIE AND RUSS HAD PROBLEMS ON
THE DIVING PORTION OF THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
IT SETTLES ON THEM HEAVIER THAN
MYSELF AND DENISE, ME AND DENISE
COULD HAVE STEPPED UP MORE AND
SAID WE KNOW WE WERE THE
SWIMMERS AND FOR US TO GO BY
THIS EVERYBODY GETS A TURN AND
IT'S FIFTH GRADE DODGEBALL
MENTALITY NEEDS TO STOP.
THE PEOPLE NEED TO STEP UP AND
THE REST OF THEM HAVE TO GO
HOME.
>> ANGIE, ARE YOU CONCERNED IT
MIGHT BE YOU TONIGHT?
>> YES, I AM.
I WAS SLOW.
BUT I WOULD HAVE DONE MY SECOND
ONE.
I REALLY WOULD HAVE BUT SHE IS
SUCH A BETTER DIVER THAN ME WHY
NOT LET HER DO IT AND GET IT
DONE FASTER.
>> WOULD IT BE FAIR TO VOTE YOU
OUT TONIGHT FOR THAT?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
RUSSELL DID THE FIRST ONE.
HE COULDN'T GET UP ON THE
LADDER.
HIS SECOND TIME HE WENT IN, HE
COMPLETELY GAVE UP.
ME, I WOULD NOT GIVE UP AND I
WANT THEM TO KNOW THAT, THAT I'M
A FIGHTER.
>> RUSSELL, ANGIE JUST CLEARLY
SAID, LISTEN, ONE THING I DIDN'T
DO IS QUIT.
RUSSELL GAVE UP.
>> NO, RUSSELL MADE A STRATEGIC
DECISION TO 1207 WHAT HE WAS
DOING, KNOWING 'TWAS GOING TO
END IN FAILURE SO WE WOULD AT
LEAST HAVE A CHANCE TO MOVE ON.
I HEAR WHAT ANGIE IS SAYING BUT
AT THE END OF THE DAY, MISS
ANGIE CAN'T HOLD A CANAL TO WHAT
I'M GOING TO BE ABLE TO OFFER
THIS TRIBE GOING FORWARD.
KNOWING THAT THERE'S 30 DAYS
LEFT TO GO, SHE AIN'T READY.
I AM.
SO LIFE EXPERIENCE, INTELLECTUAL
CAPABILITY, PHYSICAL CAPABILITY,
TO ME, THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
>> HONESTLY, JEFF, I KNOW I'M
ONLY 20 YEARS OLD AND I DON'T
HAVE THE EXPERIENCE THAT RUSSELL
HAS BUT I THINK I CAN FIGHT MORE
THAN RUSSELL, HONESTLY.
>> WHAT?
>> I WAS WILLING TO DIE FOR THIS
GAME THE LAST TIME I PLAYED.
ARE YOU WILLING TO PUT YOUR LIFE
ON THE LINE, LITTLE GIRL?
COME ON.
YOU WENT IN THAT WATER TWO FEET.
YOU WERE SLOW BECAUSE YOU DID
NOT HAVE THE PHYSICAL STRENGTH
TO GET THAT RING OFF OF THERE.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
THIS REVISIONIST HISTORY THING
YOU'RE DOING IN TERMS OF WHAT
HAPPENED ON THE PLATFORM, IT MAY
WORK HERE FOR JEFF BUT ALL OF US
WERE THERE.
WHEN YOU CAME BACK, YOU WERE
DONE.
YOU HAD GIVEN UP.
SO I MEAN, COME ON --
>> ANGIE, IS THIS HITTING HARD?
>> I FEEL THIS SMALL RIGHT NOW.
IT JUST SUCKS.
I DON'T EVER CRY.
I REALLY DON'T.
>> I THINK EVERYBODY HERE IS
SAYING THEY DO BELIEVE YOU GAVE
YOUR ALL.
I THINK WHAT RUSSELL IS SAYING
IS YOU CAN'T HOLD A CANDLE TO
ME.
>> IT'S HARD TO COMPETE WITH
HIM.
IT HONESTLY IS.
LOOK AT HIM.
>> BECAUSE THE SITUATION SHE IS
GETTING THRUST INTO A ROLE THAT
WAS PROBABLY NEVER MEANT FOR
HER, A STRENGTH ROLE.
THERE ARE LITTLE GIRLS ON THE
OTHER TRIBES THAT HAVEN'T HAD TO
DO THE THINGS SHE HAS HAD TO DO
IN TWO CHALLENGES YET.
SHE'S IN A TOUGHER SITUATION
THAN ANY OTHER YOUNG GIRL IS
RIGHT NOW.
>> SO DENY THESE THIS IS A TOUGH
VOTE.
THERE'S ONLY THE FOUR OF YOU.
YOU HAD TO HAVE MADE SOME
FRIENDSHIPS, PROBABLY ALLIANCES
AND NOW YOU HAVE THIS STRENGTH
THING BUT ALSO HAVE LOYALTY.
WHAT IF THEY CLASH?
>> DEFINITELY YOU THINK OF
LOYALTY.
ANY ALLIANCES YOU HAVE MADE YOU
HAVE TO THINK OF THAT BECAUSE
WHEN THERE'S A MERGE YOU NEED
THAT.
THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
WOULD LEAD MY VOTE MORE THAN
ANYTHING IS THE LOYALTY.
>> MALCOMB, HOW IMPORTANT IS
LOYALTY IF YOU WANT TO WIN AND
GET THE VOTES?
>> IF YOU WANT TO WIN AND GET
THE VOTES, LOYALTY IS PARAMOUNT
BUT WE HAVE TO GET TO THE POINT
WHERE YOU CAN WIN THE GAME.
SO TONIGHT'S VOTE IS A BALANCING
ACT BETWEEN STRENGTH AND
LOYALTY, WHICH ONE DO WE NEED TO
GO WITH, AND THIS IS THE
QUESTION.
WE SHOULDN'T EVEN HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT ON DAY EIGHT.
>> JEFF: OK.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
RUSSELL, YOU'RE UP.
>> I'M SORRY I MADE YOU CRY.
THAT'S THE WAY THIS GAME SEEMS
TO BE PLAYING, AND I HAVE TO
PLAY HARD OR GO HOME.
>> ONE THING ABOUT ME IS I NEVER
GIVE UP.
>> I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
>> IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO
DO SO.
OK.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ THE
ASKTION IS FINAL AND THE PERSON
VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
>> FIRST VOTE, ANGIE.
>> RUSS, ONE VOTE ANGIE, ONE
VOTE RUSS.
>> ANGIE.
TWO VOTES ANGIE, ONE VOTE RUSS.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
>> THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
SURVIVOR PHILIPPINES, ANGIE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> ANGIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
KICK SOME ASS.
>> TIME TO GO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WHILE TONIGHT'S VOTE MAY NOT
HAVE BEEN EASY, HOPEFULLY WHAT
REMAINS IS THE RIGHT COMBINATION
OF PEOPLE TO TURN THIS TRIBE
AROUND.
GRAB YOU WERE TORCHES, HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Reporter: NEXT TIME ON
CONTROLLER, JEFF PLAYS BALL WITH
TANNER.
>> HAVING HIM ON MY SIDE WILL
MAKE US BOTH PRETTY POWERFUL.
>> AND THE FATE OF MATSING COMES
DOWN TO ONE DEFINING MOMENT.
>> THIS IS IT.
ASK EL.
>> YOU KNOW IT SUCKS TO BE VOTED
OUT THIS EARLY IN THE GAME BUT I
HOPE MY TRIBE CAN GROW STRONG
FROM HERE ON OUT.
I'M THEIR BIGGEST CHEERLEADER
AND I JUST APPRECIATE LIFE SO
MUCH MORE NOW, LIKE IN MY LIFE I
JUST APPRECIATE HOW LUCKY I AM
AND IT JUST HELPED ME REALIZE
HOW BLESSED I AM TO HAVE THE
LIFE THAT I HAVE.