PREVIOUSLY ON "SURVIVOR" --
>> CONGRATULATIONS!
THE TRIBES ARE MERGING!
>> Jeff: AFTER THE TWO TRIBES
MERGED, TANDANG HAD A 7-4
ADVANTAGE OVER KALABAW.
>> MERGING WITH NUMBERS, EVEN
BETTER.
>> Jeff: WHILE EVERYONE WAS
SETTLING IN, LISA FOUND
MALCOLM'S IDOL.
>> HALLELUJAH, CHURCH LADY FOUND
IT WHO HOPEFULLY HAS A HEART.
>> ME YOU AND DENICE KNOWS.
NOBODY ELSE KNOWS.
>> Jeff: WITH THE TRIBES
MERGED, PENNER WENT TO WORK
CONVINCING R.C. AND SKEW PHONE
TURN ON THEIR OLD TRIBE.
>> YOU HAVE TO HELP HIM FEEL AS
COMFORTABLE AS HE CAN ABOUT
SLITTING THE THROATS OF THE
PEOPLE HE SPENT 17 DAYS WITH.
>> Jeff: UNFORTUNATELY FOR
PENNER, JEFF WANTED TO TAKE OUT
THE RETURNING PLAYER.
>> I'LL JOIN ANY GANG AS LONG AS
I CAN GET PENNER OUT BEFORE I
GET OUT.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
PENNER WASN'T SURE OF HIS
ALLIANCE AND DECIDED TO PLAY HIS
IDOL.
IF ANYBODY HAS AN IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME.
>> I'LL DO IT.
>> Jeff: HIS INSTINCTS WERE
CORRECT.
HIS ALLIANCE TURNED.
EIGHT PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY, R.C.
>> AND HIS ALLY R.C. WAS
BLINDSIDED.
R.C., THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TEN ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
>> SO WHAT ALL HAPPENED TODAY?
WHAT WAS THE DECISION?
>> WE WERE EXPECTING BIG NUMBERS
TO COME OUR WAY, WE EXPECTED
EIGHT AT ONE TIME AND GETTING TO
TALKING TO PEOPLE AND NUMBERS
WEREN'T THERE.
EVERYBODY WAS WISHY-WASHY.
EVERYBODY WAS TOO WISHY-WASHY.
>> I KNOW, BUT THE THE THREE OF
YOU GUYS VOTED WITH US AS
DISCUSSED FOR PETE I WOULD HAVE
USED THE IDOL AND PETE WOULD
HAVE GONE HOME AND WE WOULD HAVE
HAD THE NUMBERS.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU
GUYS WERE THINKING.
>> DOES IT HURT TO GET BETRAYD?
YEAH, OF COURSE IT DOES.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU WERE KEPT OUT OF THE
SECRET.
THERE WERE SECRETS BEING TALKED
ABOUT BEHIND YOUR BACK.
AND THE THING THAT YOU TRUSTED
WASN'T TRUE.
DID YOU VOTE FOR R.C.?
>> I DO NOT VOTE FOR R.C.
>> YOU VOTED FOR ME.
>> YEAH.
I'M GOING TO BE HONEST.
>> I APPRECIATE THE HONESTY.
WHY?
>> I HAVE MY OWN STRATEGY AND MY
OWN KIND OF PATH AND IT MAY BLOW
UP IN MY FACE AND IT MAY
BACKFIRE ON ME.
>> WELL, I MEAN, LISTEN YOU SAID
TO ME YOU WANTED TO WORK WITH
ME, WHATEVER, IT'S OKAY.
THERE'S NOTHING TO SAY.
>> AND CARTER AND I, WE TRIED TO
DRAW THE LINE THE BEST WE CAN SO
WE CAN SAVE OUR OWN ASS AND
EVERYBODY SAVES THEIR OWN ASS.
WHEN THE BIGGER PICTURE DOESN'T
COME TOGETHER, WHAT DO YOU DO?
GO DOWN WITH THE SINKING SHIP?
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
>> RIGHT.
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, NOW THAT PENNER'S
PLAYED HIS IDOL, HE DOESN'T HAVE
ANY MORE POWER THAT WAY SO WE'RE
GOING TO DO OUR BEST TO WIN THE
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY, OR AT LEAST
NOT ALLOW PENNER TO HAVE IT,
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE HIM OUT.
IN THE MEANTIME, I GAVE UP A LOT
OF POWER AND AUTHORITY WHEN I
VOTED WITH TANDANG TONIGHT.
BUT THAT'S HOW I'M GOING TO WORK
MYSELF TO THE TOP IS I'M GOING
TO USE TANDANG AGAINST
THEMSELVES, USE EVERY RESOURCE
THAT I CAN AND SEE WHERE IT GOES
FROM THERE.
SO I CAN IMAGINE HOW YOU'RE
FEELING.
BUT WHAT I'M TELLING YOU IS
DON'T -- I KNOW YOU'D NEVER
THROW THE TOWEL IN, BUT DON'T
THROW IT IN.
THERE'S CRACKS, I'M TELLING YOU.
THERE IS CRACKS.
THERE'S CRACKS AND I DON'T KNOW
IF PEOPLE ARE TELLING ME THE
TRUTH, BUT I AM NOT GOING HOME
AFTER YOU.
I AM NOT GOING HOME AFTER YOU.
>> SO WHO SHOULD WE WORK WITH?
>> I ALMOST THINK WE SHOULD JUST
WAIT FOR SOMEBODY TO SCREW UP
AND WAIT FOR A CRACK TO GET
EXPOSED.
BECAUSE THEY'RE THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
>> ALL RIGHT, MY MAN?
>> I'M NOT RESIGNED TO GOING
HOME.
THERE'S NO QUIT IN ME.
BUT THE ONLY WAY THAT I CAN GET
FURTHER NOW IS BY TAKING MY FOOT
WAY OFF THE GAS PEDAL, CLIMB
INTO THE BACKSEAT, PULL THE
BLANKET OVER MY HEAD AND HOPE
THEY FORGET I'M HERE FOR A
WHILE.
BUT THEY NOW HAVE BETRAYED ME SO
ALL BETS ARE OFF.
I HAVE NO ALLIANCES, I HAVE NO
ALLEGIANCES, I DON'T CARE.
EVERYBODY'S EQUAL.
THEY ARE ALL READY TO DIE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> I AM GOING ACT LIKE THE BIG
WHITE FISHERMAN.
LET'S SEE IF I CAN CATCH SOME.
>> SOUNDS COOL.
>> EVERYBODY IS SO GALVANIZED
AGAINST PENNER BECAUSE THEY
REALLY DON'T WANT RETURNING
PLAYERS HAVING A SECOND CHANCE.
AND THEY FEEL VERY STRONGLY THAT
THEY WANT PENNER AND SKUPIN GONE
FIRST AND SECOND.
FOR MY GAME, I WANT TO STAY WITH
TANDANG, BUT I HAVE NO QUALMS
ABOUT MAKING THIS BATTLE TO WIN
A MILLION DOLLARS A LITTLE BIT
EASIER IF IT'S WITHIN MY POWER.
WELL, WHAT'D YOU FIND?
>> I DIDN'T CATCH ANYTHING.
>> ONCE PENNER AND SKUPIN'S
GONE, JEFF, CARTER, DENICE,
MALCOLM AND I WILL THEN TARGET
THE THREE THAT EVERYBODY DOESN'T
LIKE WHICH WOULD BE ARTIS, PETE
AND ABI.
>> WE'RE PLAYING A NUMBERS GAME,
STRAIGHT-UP NUMBERS GAME, YOU
WANT TO STAY HERE AS LONG AS YOU
CAN.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO WE'RE GOING TO WORRY ABOUT
THE GROUP OF THREE WE ENDED UP
JOINING FORCES WITH AND KEEPING
AROUND.
>> PETE AND ABI AND ARTIS?
>> YEAH.
I WONDER IF THE GROUP OUTSIDE OF
THAT THREE CAN EVENTUALLY COME
TOGETHER AND TRUST EACH OTHER TO
GO AHEAD AND GET THEM ON THE
BOTTOM.
>> I LIKE THAT IDEA.
>> PETE, ABI AND ARTIS ARE ALL A
TEAM THINKING THAT THEY'RE
RUNNING THE GAME.
IT WILL BE FUN TO BREAK THAT UP.
GO AHEAD, SEE IF WE GOT ANYTHING
BIG.
>> SOME FISH!
NOW THAT SOUNDS LIKE SOME FOOD,
MAYBE.
>> LISA, SHE'S SO NAIVE AND SOFT
AND NICE.
BUT WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO JUMP ON
BOARD WITH EACH OTHER AND CARRY
THIS THING INTO A FLIP SCENARIO
WHERE WE FLIP OURSELVES FROM THE
BOTTOM TO THE TOP.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU WILL DIVIDE INTO
TWO TEAMS.
ON MY GO, ONE PERSON FROM EACH
TEAM WILL RACE OUT INTO THE
WATER CARRYING A ROPE, YOU'LL
CLIP IT TO A FISH TRAP, DIVE
DOWN, RELEASE THE BUOY AND THEN
HANG ON AS THE REST OF YOUR TEAM
PULLS YOU BACK TO SHORE.
THEN THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE SELECTED ALL FOUR
FISH TRAPS, ONE PERSON WILL DIG
INTO THE SAND TO FIND A KEY
WHICH UNLOCKS A PUZZLE FRAME.
TWO PEOPLE WILL THEN USE THE
PUZZLE SCROLLS TO SOLVE THE
PUZZLE.
FIRST TEAM TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TEAM WILL
LEAVE HERE AND BE TAKEN ON A
RIVER CRUISE THROUGH THE JUNGLE
WHERE YOU WILL ENJOY BARBECUED
RIBS.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: POTATO SALAD, CORN
BREAD.
FOR DESSERT, APPLE PIE.
YOU CAN WASH IT ALL DOWN WITH
LEMONADE AND ICED TEA.
WORTH PLAYING?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: DIVIDE UP INTO TEAMS,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR TEAM TWO
TEAMS.
THE BLUE TEAM, SKUPIN, PETE,
ARTIS, ABI AND CARTER.
THE YELLOW TEAM, JEFF, MALCOLM,
PENNER, LISA, AND DENICE.
BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST INTO THE WATER ABI AND
JEFF YOU'VE GOT TO SWIM OUT,
HOOK THAT TO YOUR FISHING TRAP,
RELEASE THE BUOY AND LET YOUR
TRIBE PULL YOU BACK.
JEFF AND HIS FISH TRAP FIRST,
ONCE HE GIVES YOU THE HIGH SIGN,
START PULLING HIM BACK.
ABI'S AT HER FISHING TRAP.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: JEFF HAS GOT IT
RELEASED.
ABI'S RELEASED.
START PULLING HER.
NEXT ONE HEADS OUT, PENNER NOW
IN THE WATER FOR THE YELLOW
TEAM.
BIG LEAD FOR PENNER RIGHT NOW.
>> PULL!
PULL!
>> Jeff: ABI'S BACK.
PENNER REACHES THE SECOND BUOY
FOR THE YELLOW TEAM.
PETE NOW GOING TO HEAD OUT FOR
THE BLUE TEAM.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: PENNER BEING PULLED
IN NOW WITH THE SECOND FISH TRAP
FOR THE YELLOW TEAM!
PETE HAS CLIPPED IN.
>> GO, PETER!
>> GO, GO, GO!
GO!
>> Jeff: LISA HEADING OUT NOW
FOR THE YELLOW TEAM.
PETE NOW BEING PULLED BACK BY
THE BLUE TEAM.
TRYING TO MAKE UP SOME TIME.
LISA SLOW IN THE WATER.
CARTER'S GOING TO HEAD OUT FOR
THE BLUE TEAM.
QUICKLY GAINING ON LISA.
CARTER'S GOING TO PASS LISA VERY
SOON.
JUST LIKE THAT, THE BLUE TEAM IS
NOW IN THE LEAD.
>> COME ON, LISA!
>> GO!
>> Jeff: CARTER WITH THE THIRD
FISH TRAP.
BLUE TEAM.
>> GO, LISA!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN NOW HEADING
OUT FOR THAT FOURTH AND FINAL
FISH TRAP.
LISA'S GOT IT RELEASED.
START PULLING, YELLOW TEAM!
>> Jeff: DENICE HEADING OUT
NOW FOR THAT FOURTH AND FINAL
FISH TRAP.
SHE'S GOT TO CATCH SKUPIN.
>> GO, BABY!
>> NO!
I CAN'T SEE IT!
>> HE DOESN'T HAVE IT.
>> DO YOU HAVE IT?
>> LET IT BACK UP.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> GO!
>> Jeff: THE YELLOW TEAM IS
NOW BACK IN THE LEAD.
SKUPIN IS STUCK IN THE WATER,
CANNOT GET HIS FINAL BUOY
RELEASED.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> PULL!
PULL!
>> GO!
>> Jeff: SKUPIN HAS HIS
RELEASED.
BLUE TEAM HAS TO START PULLING!
DENICE IS BACK WITH THAT FOURTH
AND FINAL FISH TRAP.
START DIGGING!
MALCOLM DIGGING FOR THE YELLOW
TEAM.
SKUPIN NOW COMING BACK FOR THE
BLUE TEAM.
START DIGGING!
ARTIS NOW DIGGING FOR THE BLUE
TEAM, LOOKING FOR THE KEY.
MALCOLM EXHAUSTED.
BOTH GUYS WORKING HARD FOR THIS
REWARD.
>> GOT IT!
YES!
>> Jeff: OUT OF NOWHERE ARTIS
FINDS THE KEY FOR THE BLUE TEAM.
ARTIS HAS TO GET THAT UNLOCKED
FOR THE BLUE TEAM.
ONCE HE DOES, THEY CAN START
WORKING ON THEIR PUZZLE SCROLLS.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM HAS IT FOR
THE YELLOW TEAM.
SKUPIN AND PETE WORKING ON THE
SCROLLS FOR THE BLUE TEAM.
MALCOLM HAS IT UNDONE.
YELLOW TEAM IS BACK IN IT.
ONCE AGAIN WE HAVE A CHALLENGE
GOING.
PENNER AND JEFF WORKING ON THE
SCROLLS FOR THE YELLOW TEAM.
THERE ARE EIGHT SCROLLS.
YOU HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
ORDER THEY GO IN AND PUT IT ON
YOUR PUZZLE FRAME.
PENNER GOING TO START PUTTING IT
TOGETHER NOW.
PETE THINKS HE HAS A PIECE FOR
THE BLUE TEAM.
PENNER WERE THE FIRST PIECE,
WORKING ON THE SECOND PIECE
WHILE JEFF STARTS ON THE THIRD
PIECE.
PENNER WORKING ON THE THIRD
PIECE WHILE JEFF STARTS ON THE
FOURTH PIECE.
SKUPIN AND PETE NOW WORKING ON
THEIR SECOND PIECE.
PENNER AND JEFF WORKING ON THE
FIFTH PIECE.
BLUE WORKING ON THEIR THIRD
PIECE AS JEFF STARTS ON THE
SEVENTH PIECE!
YELLOW IS RIGHT.
THEY ARE VERY CLOSE TO A NICE
AFTERNOON REWARD.
SKUPIN AND PETE, YOU'VE GOT TO
PICK IT UP!
JEFF STARTING WORK ON THE EIGHTH
PIECE.
YELLOW TEAM THINKS THEY HAVE IT.
AND THEY DO!
(SCREAMINGING)
YELLOW TEAM WINS REWARD!
YELLOW TEAM, NICE JOB.
AFTERNOON PICNIC, A LITTLE
CRUISE THROUGH THE JUNGLE.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A TASTE OF HOME
FOR ME.
A LITTLE BARBECUE, SOME CORN
BREAD.
FEEL LIKE I'M HOME FOR A LITTLE
BIT.
>> Jeff: ABI, ARTISS CARTER,
SKUPIN, PETE, GOTTING TO FOR
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
JEFF, DENICE, MALCOLM, PENNER,
LISA, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT,
GOOD AFTERNOON.
>> IT'S GOOD IT HAPPENED THAT
WAY.
EVERYTHING HAPPENS FOR A REASON.
>> I'M NOT IN THE GAME.
OH, MAN, I WANTED THAT REWARD.
BUT ON THE FLIP SIDE, I'M OUT
HERE FOR A MILLION DOLLARS.
I'M STILL IN THE GAME.
I'VE BEEN EATING BEANS AND RICE
FOR 21 DAYS, BEANS AND RICE FOR
19 MORE DAYS, NOT A PROBLEM FOR
ME.
>> YOU GUYS GOT A FOUR WITH
LISA?
>> IT'S ABI, ARTIS, PETER AND
LISA, FOUR.
AND YOU ARE YOU AND JEFF.
I GUESS YOU GUYS ARE PART OF THE
ALLIANCE, TOO.
YOU KNOW, GOING WITH PENNER.
AND THERE IS NO, LIKE,
PLACEMENT, REALLY.
I REALLY DO THINK THAT WAY.
>> YOU GUYS ARE UP THERE,
THOUGH.
THAT JUST MAKES SENSE.
ABI'S GOT A BIG MOUTH AND WHEN
ABI NEED INFORMATION, THAT'S
VERY DANGEROUS.
SO IT'S LIKE THE PUPPY YOU HAVE
TO TAKE CARE OF.
SO THIS IS WHAT I'M THINKING.
WE HAVE TANDANG NOW.
EVERYTHING'S JUST A FREE RIDE TO
HOME.
SO I'M THINKING WE HAVE TO GET
RID OF KALABAW.
SO WE -- THEY WANT TO GET RID OF
PENNER NOW, RIGHT?
AND THEN THEY WANT TO GET RID OF
SKUPIN NEXT.
BUT WHAT IF WE GET RID OF
PENNER, KEEP SKUPIN AROUND FOR A
WHILE, TAKE OUT JEFF, TAKE OUT
DENICE, THEN TAKE OUT MALCOLM
AND THEN VOTE OUT SKUPIN.
>> OKAY.
I WANT JEFF GONE.
I THINK HE'S FORMING AN ALLIANCE
WITH LISA.
EVEN THOUGH YOU THINK I'M
(BLEEP) AND YOU DON'T BELIEVE
ME.
>> WHY DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO DO
THAT?
ACTUALLY, STUFF PISSES YOU OFF,
THAT PISSES ME OFF.
STOP THAT.
ABI'S IMMATURE.
SHE THINKS EVERYBODY'S OUT TO
GET HER AND I WISH I COULD VOTE
HER OUT BUT I KNOW IF SHE'S IN
THE FINAL THREE SHE'S NOT
GETTING ANY VOTE.
>> SHOULD WE GET A LITTLE DRINK
AND A TOAST?
>> YES.
>> LET'S DO A TOAST.
HERE'S TO AN INCREDIBLE PULLOFF.
AWESOME TEAM WORK.
>> GREAT ALL THE WAY AROUND.
>> HEY, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> LICK IT OFF!
>> OH, YOU GUYS.
ON THE REWARD, IT WAS A GREAT
GROUP.
WE GOT TO GO DOWN THE RIVER AND
JUST EAT.
>> JUST A FEW RIBS, GUYS.
>> I DON'T KNOW THE IF THERE'S
ENOUGH.
>> I'M SO HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
>> LET'S JUST SAVOR BITE AFTER
BITE.
THAT'S WHO I WOULD HAVE WANTED
TO HAVE BEEN AT THAT REWARD WITH
BECAUSE THEY'RE A POSITIVE GROUP
THAT HAS MESHED TOGETHER WELL.
IT WAS NICE TO BE WITH THEM.
I FEEL HORRIBLE FOR THOSE GUYS
BACK AT CAMP BUT I'M SO THANKFUL
FOR THIS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> I REALLY AM.
>> I FEEL BADLY FOR SKUPIN,
THOUGH, BECAUSE THE ONES THAT
ARE BACK THERE, THEY FIND
SOMETHING TO BE UPSET ABOUT
AFTER EVERY CHALLENGE.
>> IT'S LIKE THERE'S JUST
NEGATIVITY, YEAH.
THERE IS A BIT OF A GOOD VERSUS
EVIL DYNAMIC THE TRIBE RIGHT
NOW.
THE EVIL THREE BEING ARTIS, ABI,
PETE.
AND THE REST OF THE TRIBE
CONSIDERING THEMSELVES THE GOOD
GUYS.
>> IF YOU GET IN THEIR LINE OF
FIRE, YOU'RE GONE.
YOU'VE GOT TO JUST KISS THEIR
LITTLE BEHINDS.
>> I HATE THAT KIND OF BULLYING
AND THAT KIND OF DESPOTIC --
LIKE A TYRANT.
>> IT'S SOMETHING PENNER IS
TRYING TO TAKE ADVANTAGE TO TURN
THE VOTE AGAINST ONE OF THE FLY
INSTEAD OF HIMSELF.
>> I HONESTLY DON'T BELIEVE THAT
I CAN WIN THE GAME AT THIS
POINT.
BUT I WOULD LIKE TO SEE ANY OF
THE FOUR OF YOU OR CARTER BE
THERE.
>> IT'S EASY FOR ME WHO'S GOT MY
HEAD ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK TO
SAY YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE A MOVE.
BUT I'M SAYING IT.
AND IF IT CAN HELP SAVE ME FOR
ONE MORE VOTE I'D APPRECIATE IT
AND I THINK I CAN HELP YOU GUYS
GET IN CONTROL OF THE GAME.
I'M NEXT MANY THE CROSS FIRE,
THEN SKUPIN, THEN PROBABLY YOU,
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT A WAYS TO
GO.
HONESTLY, THERE MUST BE A WAY TO
DIFFUSE THAT AND SAY WE CAN'T
LIVE IN A CAMP WITH TYRANNICAL
BULLIES, IT'S JUST NOT COOL.
>> CERTAINLY THE IDEA OF
BATTLING IT OUT AT THE END WITH
FOUR OTHER WORTHY OPPONENTS IS
SUCH A NOBLE CHOICE.
BUT I'M DISCOVERING THAT I'M NOT
TRYING TO JUST GET TO THE FINAL
FIVE.
I'M TRYING TO WIN, WHICH MEANS I
NEED TO FIRST GET TO THE FINAL
THREE WITH AS MANY PEOPLE THAT
AREN'T GOING TO GET MORE VOTES
THAN ME AS POSSIBLE.
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST HOW YOU GET
AHEAD.
THE SAME RULES DON'T APPLY IN
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR" AS THEY
DO IN REAL LIFE.
PENNER GOES HOME, SOMEBODY'S
GOING TO WAKE UP AND REALIZE
THIS IS THE TIME TO DO A 5-4
ALLIANCE.
IT MAKES MUCH MORE SENSE FOR ME
AND SKUPIN TO GO TO THE END WITH
ABI AND ARTIS AND PETE BECAUSE
THEY HAVE MADE SO MANY ENEMIES
AND MADE SO MANY HOT HEAD
EMOTIONAL MOVES THAT HAVE TICKED
PEOPLE OFF.
>> PENNER, I GOT A PRETTY GOOD
CLAM.
>> I HAVE A PLAN THAT ASSURES
HIM THAT HE DOES NOT NEED TO
SCRAMBLE AND MAKE ALLIANCES WITH
SOMEBODY ELSE THAT'S GOING TO
PROMISE HIM THE WORLD BECAUSE
I'M GOING TO PROMISE HIM THE
UNIVERSE.
I WANT TO TELL YOU MY PLAN.
I'LL LOOK YOU IN THE EYES AND I
HAVE NOT TOLD ANYBODY THIS PLAN.
YOU KNOW PENNER NOW AND THEN
EVERYBODY'S ON BOARD FOR YOU
NEXT.
BUT MALCOLM HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> WOW.
>> AND NOBODY KNOWS IT EXCEPT
MALCOLM AND DENICE AND ME.
HE HASN'T TOLD ANYBODY ELSE.
AFTER PENNER WE'VE GOT TO GET
PETE ON THAT WE HAVE TO HAVE
YOU.
5-4.
TANDANG HAS TO HANG TOGETHER AND
BLIND SIDE MALCOLM.
>> LISA IS NOW IN THIS GAME TO
WIN IT.
WHICH IS GREAT.
BECAUSE SHE'S MY CLOSEST ALLY
OUT HERE.
WHAT HAPPENS TONIGHT IF PENNER
WINS IMMUNITY?
>> I THINK -- I THINK -- COME
IN.
WE'RE HAVING A VERY HEATED
DISCUSSION AND IT'S ALL ABOUT
YOU.
>> HOT DISCUSSION?
>> A HEATED AND HOT DISCUSSION.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO BREAK IT UP,
I'M SORRY.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
THIS IS MY BUDDY.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND I KNOW IT'S --
>> WELL, MAYBE -- MAYBE HE'LL
WIN IMMUNITY.
NO, YOU WON'T, DUDE, BECAUSE I'M
WINNING IMMUNITY TODAY.
SO IT'S YOUR TURN TONIGHT.
>> A LOT WILL DEPEND ON WHO WINS
IMMUNITY.
THE ONLY WAY TO BE SAFE IS TO
WIN IT.
AND SO YOU'RE GOING TO SEE A DOG
FIGHT OUT THERE TODAY.
>> I'VE NEVER WON AN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
NEVER ONCE.
SO MAYBE -- MAYBE IT'S HIGH TIME
THAT JOHNNY DID.
>> JONATHAN, ALREADY.
>> STICK IT RIGHT IN THEIR DAMN
FACES.
STICK IT IN THEIR FACES AND I'D
SAY FOR ONCE OF THE THREE TIMES
IF I COULD WIN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: FIRST THING'S FIRST,
I'LL TAKE BACK THE NECKLACES.
THANK YOU, DENICE.
HARD TO GIVE IT UP.
CARTER.
ONLY NEED ONE TODAY.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU WILL
RACE OVER AND UNDER A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES COLLECTING BAGS OF
PUZZLE PIECES AS YOU GO.
THE FIRST THREE TO CROSS THE
LINE AND MOVE ON TO THE FINAL
ROUND WHERE YOU WILL USE THOSE
PIECES TO SOLVE A SNAKE PUZZLE.
BIG STAKES FOR THE WINNER.
IMMUNITY AND A GUARANTEED 1-9
SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
TEAR THROUGH THOSE KNOTS.
GET YOUR FINGERS IN THERE, RIP
THEM OPEN!
GET THE BAG AND GET OVER THAT
FIRST OBSTACLE.
ABI, JEFF, PETE OVER QUICKLY.
ARTIS IS OVER.
THERE GOES SKUPIN AND PENNER.
DENICE, CARTER AND LISA.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON BAG TWO
NOW.
THREE PEOPLE ARE MOVING ON.
THAT'S IT.
ONLY THREE.
YOU WANT IT TO BE YOU.
PETE IS FIRST OVER WITH THE
SECOND BAG.
JEFF RIGHT BEHIND WITH HIS
PETE IS WORKING ON HIS FINAL
BAG.
THERE GOES MALCOLM, SKUPIN,
ARTIS AND PENNER'S IN THERE.
ABI, DENICE, CARTER AND LISA
FALLING BEHIND.
IT IS PETE, MALCOLM, SKUPIN,
ARTIS, PENNER AND JEFF LOOKING
FOR THREE.
PETE HAS IT.
PETE IS ACROSS.
HE'S MOVING ON.
JEFF IS ACROSS.
ONE MORE SPOT!
COMING DOWN TO PENNER AND
SKUPIN!
MOVE!
VERY CLOSE.
PENNER MOVING ON!
PETE, JEFF, AND PENNER MOVING ON
TO THE FINAL ROUND.
HERE WE GO.
IT IS PETE, PENNER, AND JEFF
LOOKING FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
GO, GUYS!
GO, GUYS, COME ON!
>> Jeff: THIS IS POTENTIALLY A
MILLION-DOLLAR PUZZLE FOR ONE OF
YOU.
>> GO, JEFF, GO, PETE!
>> Jeff: IT'S A VERY CLEAR
PATTERN THAT YOU CAN USE AS A
GUIDE.
PETE OFF TO A QUICK START.
JEFF OFF TO A GOOD START.
PENNER KIND OF PLACING PIECES
WHEREVER HE CAN FIND THEM.
PETE PLACES ANOTHER PIECE.
>> COME ON PETE, COME ON.
>> Jeff: PENNER TRYING TO
FORCE ONE.
JEFF WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> COME ON, JEFF!
>> Jeff: JEFF'S STARTING TO
GET A LITTLE MOMENTUM NOW.
>> COME ON, JEFF!
>> Jeff: RIGHT NOW IT'S JEFF
AND PETE VYING FOR IMMUNITY.
PENNER FALLING A LITTLE BEHIND.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: PUZZLE'S TAKE A LONG
TIME AND ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
PETE WORKING STRAIGHT FROM THE
FRONT.
>> PETE LOOKS GOOD.
>> SO DOES PENNER, ACTUALLY.
>> Jeff: PENNER WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
>> MAN, THAT EAST'D BE CRAZY.
>> Jeff: PEN WE ARE ANOTHER
PIECE!
PENNER IS BACK IN THIS.
>> COME ON JEFF.
>> IT IS JEFF, PENNER AND PETE
IN THAT ORDER.
PENNER WITH ANOTHER PIECE!
AND ANOTHER PIECE.
PENNER'S ON A ROLL.
>> COME ON, JEFF!
>> Jeff: JEFF PICKING UP THE
PACE.
PENNER STARTING TO PULL AWAY OUT
OF NOWHERE!
>> COME ON, JEFF.
>> CONCENTRATE!
>> Jeff: JEFF TRYING TO CATCH
UP.
>> Jeff: PENNER DOWN TO TWO
PIECES LEFT.
PENNER WINS IMMUNITY!
LIVES TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
>> HO!
>> Jeff: PENNER, COME ON OVER.
>> FIRST TIME EVER.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
>> YUP.
>> YEAH, WHAT A JOKE.
>> Jeff: NICE JOB.
PENNER SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 22
DIFFICULT DAYS IN THE
PHILIPPINES, SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL, CONGRATS.
>> THANKS, BUDDY.
ABOUT THAT CHALLENGE.
THAT WAS MAYBE THE BEST THING I
EVER DID IN MY LIFE.
I HAVE TO DIG DEEP.
>> SAVE IT FOR THE END.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, MAN.
>> WHEN YOU NEEDED IT MOST,
THAT'S THE TIME TO GET IT.
>> FIRST EVER.
>> GOING INTO THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, ALL ANYONE'S TALKING
ABOUT IS DON'T LET JONATHAN
PENNER WIN IMMUNITY.
OF COURSE, MURPHY'S LAW STATES
THAT HAS TO HAPPEN SO I DON'T
KNOW WHY I'M SO SURPRISED
JONATHAN PENNER WON IMMUNITY
TODAY.
HE JUST THREW EVERYONE'S PLANS
FOR A LOOP AND NOW WE'RE HAVING
TO DO A BABY SCRAMBLE BACK AT
CAMP TO FIGURE OUT WHO WE'RE
GOING TO GET RID OF INSTEAD OF
PENNER.
>> IT'S THE SAME THING, JUST A
DIFFERENT ORDER.
>> SKUPIN?
YOU LET ME KNOW IF IT'S ANY
DIFFERENT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> MAKING SURE WE'RE COVERED
HERE.
WE WERE SO FOCUSED ON PENNER.
>> OKAY, JUST LET ME KNOW.
>> THIS IS GOING TO MAKE FOR A
LONG DAY.
>> YOU GUYS THINKING TONIGHT?
>> HE CAN KEEP TALKING THROUGH
HIS IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
WHATEVER.
>> WHAT DO WE TELL SKUPIN?
>> SKUPIN KNOWS.
>> HE HAS TO KNOW.
HE'S JUST BEING MELLOW.
I MEAN, IT SUCKS BUT --
>> IT JUST THROWS A WRINKLE INTO
POTENTIALLY --
>> GOD, THAT SUCKS.
>> YUP, MY VOTE'S GOING TO BE
FOR SKUPIN TONIGHT BECAUSE
PENNER KIND OF DONE THE
UNTHINKABLE.
HE'S WON TWO CHALLENGES IN A
ROW-- ONE ON MY TEAM AND NOW ONE
BY HIMSELF.
SO HE'S JUST BOUGHT HIMSELF
ANOTHER THREE DAYS OF A DEAD MAN
WALKING.
WELL, SORRY, MAN, THAT'S THE
WORST THING THAT CAN HAPPEN TO
YOU.
>> NO SECRET.
NO SECRET AT ALL.
>> TOO BAD.
I WAS REALLY WANTING THE
OPPORTUNITY BUT -.
>> MALCOLM HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL FOR MATSING.
THE VERY FIRST DAY OF THE MERGE,
THIS WAS VERY INNOCENT ON MY
PART, I WAS SIMPLY TAKING ALL
THE CLOTHES OUT TO LET THEM DRY,
IT FOUND IN THE HIS BAG ON THE
FIRST DAY OF THE MERGE.
I TOLD HIM I WOULDN'T TELL
ANYBODY AND I HAVEN'T.
BUT THE ONLY WAY TO GET RID OF
HIM IS TO BLIND SIDE HIM SO HE
HAS TO THINK HE'S REALLY, REALLY
SAFE.
WE HAVE TO BLIND SIDE MALCOLM
TONIGHT SO YOU HAVE TO REALIZE
WHATEVER HE SAYS, HIS ALLEGIANCE
IS WITH THEM, NOT WITH US.
>> RIGHT.
THIS WHOLE ENTIRE PLAN, GETTING
RID OF MALCOLM AND HIM HAVING
THE IDOL, I GOT COMPLETELY
BLINDSIDED BY THAT BECAUSE I
ACTUALLY KIND OF TRUSTED MALCOLM
MALCOLM.
THIS PLAN RIGHT NOW IS LISA'S
PLAN.
IS IT A GOOD PLAN?
IS IT A PLAN THAT'S ACTUALLY
GOING TO BE EFFECT I HAVE
BECAUSE MALCOLM DOES HAVE AN
IDOL AND MALCOLM IS PLAYING TWO
SIDES?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE GOING WHO W MATSING?
>> UH-HUH.
>> YOU SURE?
>> NO, NO, IF I HAD THAT THING
MY PULSE WOULD HAVE BEEN MUCH
LOWER GOING TO YOUR TRIBE A FEW
WEEKS AGO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SOMEBODY SAID I DID.
>> SOMEONE SAID YOU DID.
>> WHO SAID I DID?
>> LISA.
SHE SAYS YOU APPARENTLY HAVE THE
IDOL AND THAT'S THE WAY TO FISH
YOU OUT.
>> PETE CONFRONTS ME ABOUT THE
IDOL AND MY FIRST THOUGHT IS
JUST LIE, LIE, LIE, LIE.
BUT ALREADY MY HEART'S IN MY
STOMACH BECAUSE IF THAT RUMOR IS
OUT THERE IT'S GOING TO COME OUT
EVENTUALLY THAT I ACTUALLY TO
HAVE THE THING.
>> SO I HAVE TO GO SCRAMBLE FOR
IT NOW.
>> NO, DON'T SCRAMBLE.
I CAN SAVE YOU.
>> WHY NOT SEND HOME JEFF?
>> YOU WANT TO VOTE JEFF NOW?
>> THERE'S ENOUGH PEOPLE, LIKE
-- WE CAN SWITCH IT REALLY
QUICK.
>> I'LL GO JEFF IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT ME TO DO.
>> THERE'S GOING TO BE FIVE
PEOPLE GOING.
>> JEFF'S BEHIND YOU.
>> MALCOLM FREAKED OUT AND -- I
MEAN, THAT RIGHT THERE WAS
ENOUGH OF A REACTION TO JUST
KIND OF KNOW -- LOOK INTO HIS
SOUL AND BE LIKE HE DOESN'T HAVE
THE IDOL.
SO I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT
LISA'S TRYING TO PULL HERE.
>> SO SHE'S SAYING I HAVE AN
IDOL FROM THE ORIGINAL MATSING.
>> SHE NEVER SAID THAT TO ME.
>> WELL, SHE TOLD ENOUGH PEOPLE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE IT?
I WAS GOING TO SAY PLAY IT IF
YOU GOT IT.
>> I HAD NO IDEA THIS WAS GOING
ON.
>> YUP.
>> SO WHAT'S THE VOTE?
>> JEFF.
>> JEFF?
IS IT JEFF?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WE JUST NEED TO CHILL OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
I THOUGHT EVERYTHING WAS FINE
FIVE MINUTES AGO.
>> RIGHT NOW WE'RE VOTING OUT
JEFF.
I WANTED JEFF OUT SECOND ANYWAY.
IF PENNER LOST I WOULD HAVE KEPT
SKUPIN AROUND AS THE SWING VOTE
BUT RIGHT NOW JEFF'S GOING HOME.
HE'S A NICE GUY, HE'S PLAYED A
GREAT GAME BUT HE'S A BIG THREAT
AND I WANT HIM GONE.
>> OKAY, SO -- MALCOLM'S GOING
ASK IF I SAID -- TOLD YOU ABOUT
THE IDOL.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND DID YOU TELL HIM THAT I
TOLD YOU?
>> NO.
I JUST TOLD HIM THAT WE KNOW.
HE SAYS HE DOESN'T HAVE IT.
>> AND WHAT'D YOU SAY?
>> I JUST -- I WASING.
>> WAIT A SECOND, DON'T GO YET.
(SIGHS)
WELL, MALCOLM PULLED PETE ASIDE,
PETE WAS THROWN OFF GUARD AND
WASN'T VERY GOOD AT CONVINCING
HIM THAT HIS NAME WASN'T ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK SO EVERYTHING
JUST HIT THE FAN.
ARE THEY WANTING TO VOTE ME NOW?
>> NO.
UH-UH.
IT WOULD BE JEFF.
I THINK WE SHOULD JUST VOTE HIM
OUT.
PLAYING THE MASTERMIND ROLE IS
VERY HARD WORK.
IT'S NOT EASY.
AND YOU NEVER REALLY KNOW YOU'RE
THE MASTERMIND.
IT'S JUST THAT LAST -- RIGHT
BEFORE TRIBAL IS WHEN YOU REALLY
FIGURE OUT DO YOU REALLY HAVE
EVERYBODY AND IS IT SOLID.
>> WATCH OUT, JEFF'S BEHIND YOU.
>> SOME GOSSIP GOING ON AROUND
HERE?
WHAT THE HELL?
>> WE'RE BOTH BEING TOSSED
AROUND RIGHT NOW.
>> WE COULD GET SIX RIGHT NOW.
>> SKUPIN, DENICE, PENNER,
CARTER WILL GO?
>> YEAH.
>> I SAY WE DO IT RIGHT NOW.
>> WE WERE ALL SET TO GO AHEAD
AND LET SKUPIN GO BUT NOW I
FOUND OUT THEY WERE GUNNING FOR
ME.
BUT HOPEFULLY THE BULLET'S GOING
TO GO IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
>> EITHER PETER OR ABI?
>> PETE?
>> WE COULD CUT THE HEAD OF THE
SNAKE OFF RIGHT NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> TALK TO DENICE.
>> DENICE, SIX PEOPLE ARE VOTING
PETE TONIGHT.
WHICH AM ANY.
>> ME, YOU, JEFF, PENNER,
CARTER.
>> OKAY.
>> SKUPIN.
>> OKAY, GOT IT.
>> LET'S GET A TARP UP ON THIS
TREE RIGHT HERE.
>> WE ALL KNOW IT HAS TO BE DONE
AT SOME POINT.
WE'VE ALL BEEN TALKING ABOUT IT.
>> PETE'S GOING HOME.
WE GOT ALL SIX VOTES.
>> I THOUGHT THEY WERE SENDING
YOU HOME TONIGHT.
>> EVERYBODY'S GOING MAD IN THE
PAST HOUR.
LISA RAN HER MOUTH ABOUT MY
IDOL, I'M PLAYING DUMB TRYING TO
PLAY IN THIS VOTE, BUT IT'S
COMING WITH ME TONIGHT.
IF THIS THING EVEN SEEMS CLOSE
I'M PLAYING IT.
I'M VOTING FOR PETE RIGHT NOW.
CUT THE HEAD OFF THE SNAKE.
THIS IS NOT THE WAY I SAW IT
GOING AT ALL.
I WANTED TO TRY TO GET RID OF
SKUPIN BUT IT'S GOING TO BE HELL
NO MATTER WHAT WE DO.
THIS IS THE MOST LAST-MINUTE
CRAZY THING I'VE EVER BEEN A
PART OF IN MY LIFE.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
R.C. VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> RIGHT ON.
>> Jeff: SO AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL THERE WAS A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT RETURNING PLAYERS NOT
BEING WELCOMED.
SO SKUPIN, THE MINUTE PENNER
WINS IMMUNITY DOES THAT POINT
THE FINGER THEN AT YOU?
>> I FELT A LOT OF PRESSURE
INSTANTLY.
BUT WHEN I CAME BACK TO CAMP, IT
TOOK A LITTLE BIT OF THE
PRESSURE OFF WHEN I HEARD SOME
PEOPLE TALKING.
(LAUGHS)
>> Jeff: MALCOLM?
>> I PUT MY FAITH IN A LITTLE
TEXAS GIRL AND SHE THREW ME
UNDER THE BUS PRETTY HARD TODAY.
>> Jeff: LISA?
THREW SOMEONE UNDER THE BUS?
>> THAT IS ABSOLUTELY TRUE.
IT WAS GOING TO BE AN EASY VOTE
UNTIL PENNER WON IMMUNITY.
BACKUP PLAN WAS MICHAEL.
BUT MICHAEL HAS BEEN THE STRONG
MEMBER OF THE TANDANG TRIBE FROM
THE VERY BEGINNING SO WHY NOT
ELIMINATE WHOM I THOUGHT WAS THE
BIGGEST THREAT IN THE GAME--
WHICH WOULD BE MALCOLM.
>> Jeff: SO IF WE JUST LOOK AT
IT FROM HERE, THERE'S THE
TANDANG FIVE-- LISA, ABI, PETE,
SKUPIN, AND ARTIS-- AND THEN
THERE'S THE KALABAW FOUR--
PENNER, JEFF, DENICE, AND
CARTER.
AND THEN THERE'S YOU, MALCOLM.
DENICE, DOES THAT GIVE YOU SOME
HOPE THAT, HEY, THERE'S OUR
FIFTH RIGHT THERE AND WE'RE
SQUARE UP 5-5 AGAIN?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
EVERY CRACK IS AN OPPORTUNITY.
>> Jeff: SO ABI, IT HAS TO
GIVE YOU A BIT OF CONCERN TO
FIND OUT THAT ONE OF YOUR TRIBE
MEMBERS JUST SCREW IT HAD WHOLE
GAME UP.
>> YES, AND I ALWAYS FELT THAT
MALCOLM WAS A PART OF US SO I AM
IN AWE RIGHT NOW.
I THINK THIS IS REALLY
LUDICROUS.
>> BUT YOU WERE WILLING FOR
MICHAEL TO GO HOME WHO WAS PART
OF THE TANDANG TRIBE ORIGINALLY.
>> BUT MICHAEL AND R.C. WAS
ALWAYS ON THE OUTSIDE.
IT WAS ALWAYS YOU, ME, PETER AND
ARTIS.
AND MALCOLM WAS ALWAYS PART OF
OUR ALLIANCE AS WELL.
>> BUT YOU JUST --
>> Jeff: IT MIGHT BE TOO LATE
FOR THAT ONE ABI.
>> I THINK THAT WAS A MISTAKE.
I'M SORRY.
MALCOLM WAS WAY STRONGER IN OUR
ALLIANCE THAN SKUPIN EVER WAS.
>> BUT IF SOMEBODY HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL YOU TRY TO FLUSH
IT OUT OR TRUE TRY TO BLIND SAID
THEM BECAUSE IT'S A HUGE THREAT
IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: SO, LISA, YOU'RE
SAYING MALCOLM HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU KNOW IT?
>> YES.
AND I DID BRING THAT INFORMATION
TO MAKE THE TANDANG TRIBE
STRONGER.
I WAS PLAYING BOTH SIDES, BUT MY
ALLEGIANCE WAS TO THE ORIGINAL
ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: OH.
>> JUST TO CLEAR THE AIR.
THERE'S WAY TOO MUCH CHAOS
TONIGHT.
I'M NOT GOING HOME.
SO THIS THING IS GETTING PLAYED.
IT'S PUT A TARGET ON MY BACK.
I'M NOT DEALING WITH IT ANYMORE
AND IF ANYBODY'S JUMPED ON
LISA'S BOAT AND DECIDES TO VOTE
FOR ME, YOU MIGHT BE IN FOR A
MEAN SURPRISE IN A SECOND.
>> Jeff: ANYBODY ELSE WANT TO
REVEAL THEY HAVE AN IDOL?
GET IT OUT?
>> I HAVE IT, YES.
I HAVE IT.
>> THIS IS AWESOME!
I WAS SELFLESSLY HAVING THIS TO
PROTECT PEOPLE IN MY ALLIANCE.
HERE, EVERYONE.
>> GREAT TRIBAL.
>> FANTASTIC, MAN!
>> Jeff: WOW.
I DON'T EVEN REALLY KNOW WHAT TO
SAY MYSELF BEFORE WE GO TO THE
VOTE.
>> WELL, I'D LIKE TO ASK
SOMETHING.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE COULD BE SIX
OF US RIGHT HERE WHO CAN MARCH
FORWARD IN THIS GAME.
THAT MEANS KEEPING SKUPIN AND I
IN THAT SIX, AT LEAST FOR A
WHILE.
YOU GUYS READY TO DO THAT?
>> WE'VE DISCUSSED THOSE OPTIONS
AND MANY MORE.
I THINK YOU ALREADY KNOW ABOUT
THAT.
>> YES.
>> OKAY.
YOU GUYS READY TO DO THAT,
CARTER?
SKUPIN?
>> WOW.
>> WELL, I WOULD LIKE TO AT
LEAST MAKE MY PROPOSAL AND THAT
IS ANYBODY I HAVE GIVEN MY WORD
TO WE CAN STILL KEEP THE
MAJORITY IF WE GO WITH PLAN "B"
AND HOPEFULLY THIS PROVES I AM
LOYAL ENOUGH TO TAKE THE
OFFENSIVE MOVE FOR US TO SECURE
THE NUMBERS OF THOSE WHO ARE IN
OUR CORE ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: SO IT SOUNDS LIKE
THERE ARE TWO PITCHES: LISA'S
SAYING PLA PLAN "B"--
INVOLVES ONE OF THOSE SIX.
PENNER'S SAYING LET'S TAKE THE
SIX AND VOTE OUT EITHER LISA,
ABI, PETE OR ARTIS.
>> I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE COMING
AFTER ME.
>> Jeff: WHY YOU?
>> MY NAME'S BEEN THROWN AROUND
THE ISLAND THE ENTIRE TIME WE'VE
MERGED SO IT'S PROBABLY ME.
>> AND MY NAME'S BEEN THROWN
UNDER THE HAT AS MUCH AS PETE'S,
SO'S MALCOLM'S.
AND PENNER AND SKUPIN.
AND LEE'S SAA'S PROBABLY ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK AND NOW ABI, TOO.
THIS IS PRETTY FUN, JEFF.
>> Jeff: I'VE GOT TO SAY, I
DIDN'T THINK OF A MORE
COMPLICATED TRIBAL COUNCIL EVER
IN MY TIME OF TRIBAL.
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ARTIS, YOU'RE UP.
>> WELL, I SAID YOU WERE PLAN
"B" BUT I THINK THIS WAS
ACTUALLY PLAN D OR PLAN E.
>> PETE, IT WAS FANTASTIC TO
WATCH YOUR LITTLE AHRAOEUBS JUST
KIND OF IMPLODE ON ITSELF.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW IS MOST DEFINITELY THE TIME
TO DO SO.
NOBODY PLAYING THEIR IDOL?
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE RED,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ABI.
JEFF.
PETE.
ONE VOTE ABI, ONE VOTE JEFF, ONE
VOTE PETE.
JEFF.
TWO VOTES JEFF.
PETE.
TWO VOTES JEFF; TWO VOTES PETE;
ONE VOTE ABI.
JEFF.
THREE VOTES JEFF.
PETE.
THREE VOTES JEFF; THREE VOTES
PETE, ONE VOTE ABI.
JEFF.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JEFF.
PETE.
FOUR VOTES PETE.
FOUR VOTES JEFF.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JEFF.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JEFF, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
THAT VOTE MAY GO DOWN AS ONE OF
THE BIGGEST BLOWN OPPORTUNITIES
IN THE HISTORY OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR".
>> HOW CAN WE STAY LOYAL TO
SOMEBODY WHO'S NOT LOYAL TO US?
>> AFTER BEING BULLIED BY HER
ALLIANCE --
>> I THINK YOU'RE JUST GULLIBLE.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BRING THAT UP
AGAIN.
I'M JUST LETTING YOU GO.
>> Jeff: LISA TURNS TO PENNER.
>> DEVASTATING.
NOW YOU KNOW.
>> Jeff: AND COULD FLIP
EVERYTHING UPSIDE DOWN.
>> MAYBE IT MAKES SENSE TO GO
WITH THE OTHER ALLIANCE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT PISSES ME OFF
IS I THINK I'VE MADE ABOUT $60
MILLION PLAYING BASEBALL AND I
WANT THIS FREAKING MILLION
DOLLARS IN THIS GAME!
AND IT'S NOT EVEN A MILLION
BUCKS, IT'S $600,000 BY THE TIME
OBAMA TAKES IT.
I'M A GAME SEVEN WORLD SERIES
LOSER.
I'VE PLAYED IN THE BIGGEST GAMES
IN THE WORLD AND THE WORST GAMES
IN THE WORLD BUT THIS JUST
SUCKS.