>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": IN A BATTLE BETWEEN
THREE TRIBES, MAT SING WAS THE
ONLY TRIBE TO PERFECT THE ART OF
FARR.
>> I'M SICK OF THIS.
EITHER GO HARD OR GO HOME.
>> MAT SING WINLESS!
>> THEY'VE LOST THREE CHALLENGES
IN A ROW.
>> ONE WIN IS ALL IT WILL TAKE
TO KNOW WE'RE NOT DESTINED FOR
ANNIHILATION.
>> Jeff: THEY WERE THE ONLY
TRIBE NOT TO HAVE FOUND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> UNTIL MY TORCH IS SNUFFED, I
AM GOING TO NEED IT.
>> FORICAL BOW AND TANDANG,
THEIR WINNING STREAK COULD NOT
HIDE THE CRACKS.
PENNER USED HIS IDOL TO FORM A
SECRET ALLIANCE OF MEN.
>> LET'S RIDE TOGETHER AND SEE
WHERE WE GO.
>> Jeff: THE WOMEN JOINED
FORCES AGAINST THE MEN.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE A FEMALE.
THAT'S THE WORST THING YOU CAN
DO TO A WOMAN.
>> OH, MY GOD, I FOUND IT.
>> Jeff: THEY STARTED A
MAJORITY ALLIANCE WITH LISA AND
ARTIS.
AT THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, FOR
THE FOURTH TIME IN A ROW--
>> THIS IS IT!
>> Jeff: MAT SING LOST, AND
RUSSELL LOST IT.
>> I DON'T GET WHAT'S HAPPENING,
FAWCT.
MALCOLM AND DENISE VOTED OUT THE
FIRST RETURNING PLAYER.
RUSS, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU'RE DOWN TO TWO.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU GOTTA DO, KEEP
FIGHTING.
14 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT OPINION
>> WE'RE DOWN TO TWO MEMBERS ON
DAY 10 ALREADY.
I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT HAPPEN ON
DAY 39, NOT-- NOT A WEEK AND A
HALF INTO THE GAME.
>> OH, IT'S JUST SO COLD.
>> THIS IS SERIOUSLY GOING TO BE
THE COLDEST NIGHT.
>> YUP.
>> IT'S NOT TOTALLY
UNPRECEDENTED TO HAVE ONE TRIBE
SO LOW, BUT THIS EARLY ON, WE
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO EXPECT OR
WHAT'S GOING TO GET THROWN AT
US.
>> YOU, THE ONE TRIBE, ME THE
OTHER TRIBE.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING I CAN
THINK OF IS ALL OF A SUDDEN IT
WILL BE MIXED.
>> EVERYONE LOVES AN UNDERDOG SO
YOU'RE RIGHT.
TWO AGAINST 12?
THE ODDS ARE LONG BUT I WOULDN'T
COUNT US OUT JUST YET.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> MOSQUITOES
>> I KNOW.
>> COME ORAIN, STOP FOR A LITTLE
BIT.
THE RAIN DIDN'T LET UP ALL
NIGHT.
WE DON'T HAVE A TARP.
WE HAVEN'T WON ANYTHING.
SO IT WAS JUST US IN THE FETAL
POSITION WAITING FOR THE SUN TO
COME UP.
>> MALCOLM, WE'VE GOT MAIL.
>> WE'RE ABOUT AS OWN DOWNAND
OUT AS YOU POSSIBLY CAN GET AT
THIS POINT.
>> LIVING FROM THE SEA AND
LIVING OFF THE LAND.
>> WE HAVE A REWARD CHALLENGE
TODAY, TWO OF US AGAINST TWO
TRIBES OF SIX.
IT SEEMS LIKE A GOOD TIME FOR
SOME SORT OF TRIBE MIX-UP OR
SWAP OR JUST BE ABSORBED.
IF WE'RE NOT COMING BACK TO OUR
BEACH THIS MIGHT BE THE LAST
CHANCE TO LOOK FOR THE IDOL.
>> I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN NOW THAT WE'RE DOWN TO
TWO.
MAYBE IT'S GOING TO BE, LIKE, A
RESHUFFLING OF THE DECK.
BUT THE IMMUNITY IDOL IS STILL
HERE, SO WE STARTED LOOKING ALL
OVER.
IF IT'S IN OUR CAMP, WHERE WOULD
IT BE?
>> THE TREES-- THE BASKET WAS
ALWAYS HERE.
>> THERE'S NOTHING IN HERE BUT
RICE.
THIS SHOULD NOT BE THAT
COMPLICATED.
WE'RE DIGGING UP EVERY POINT OF
INTEREST AROUND OUR CAMP, TRYING
TO FIND THIS DAMN THING.
I'M GOING TO BURN THE DAMN THING
DOWN UNTIL I FIND IT.
I FEEL LIKE A PLOOEP IDIOL YOT.
IT'S NOT RICE.
>> I'M CLUELESS.
>> LET ME SEE THAT THING REAL
QUICK.
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> I MEAN-- I CHECKED EVERY PART
ON THIS BASKET, RIGHT?
>> PLEASE TELL ME THAT IS IT.
THANK YOU!
>> OH!
>> THIS IS HUGE PEE WEHAVE NO
STAKE GOING FORWARD EXCEPT EACH
OTHER AGAINST 12 OTHER PEOPLE.
THIS IS LEVERAGE?
THIS GIVES ME A HUGE AMOUNT OF
POWER IN THIS GAME.
IT'S BEEN SO TOUGH FOR A WEEK
AND A HALF.
NOW I'M GIDDY LIKE A SCHOOL
YEAR.
OH, MY GOD.
>> WE DID JUST FIND HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT WAS FRUSTRATING BECAUSE IF
WE'RE ABSORBED INTO THE SAME
TRIBE, GREAT.
WE CAN FIGURE OUT A WAY TO USE
IT TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
IF WE'RE SPLIT, MALCOLM'S GOT
THE IDOL IN HIS POSSESSION, AND
I HAVEN'T FOUND MY OWN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
KALABAW AND TANDANG GETTING YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW MASTING
TRIBE.
RUSSELL VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND WITH THAT, MASTING IS DOWN
TO TWO TRIBE MEMBERS LEFT,
MALCOLM AND DENISE.
LISA, DO YOU STILL LOOK AT THEM
AS A TRIBE BEING DECIMATED OR IS
THAT DONE AND WE'RE NOW LEFT
WITH TWO INDIVIDUALS FIGHTING TO
STAY ALIVE IN THIS GAME?
>> I THINK YOU CAN LOOK AT IT AS
A TRIBE THAT IS DECIMATE OR TWO
PEOPLE WHO HAVE PREVAILED.
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN. BUFFS.
MASTING HAS BEEN DECIMATED.
MASTING IS NO MORE.
MALCOLM AND DENISE, YOU'RE GOING
TO JOIN EITHER TANDANG OR
KALABAW.
WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUT RIGHT
NOW.
>> OH, YES!
>> Jeff: THERE ARE TWO BUFFS.
THEY'RE WRAPPED.
>> DO YOU WANT TO SWITCH OR NOT?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> Jeff: AND THE SUSPENSE.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM GOES TO
TANDANG.
>> WHOOO!
>> Jeff: DENISE GOES TO
KALABAW.
>> WELCOME!
>> THANK YOU!
>> Jeff: SO WE HAVE TWO TRIBES
NOW, TANDANG VERSUS KALABAW.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE STARTING OVER IN
A SENSE.
YOU READY TO GET TO YOUR FIRST
REWARD CHALLENGE AS NEW TRIBES?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
WE'RE GOING TO SQUARE OFF ONE ON
ONE.
YOU WILL EACH BE HOLDING AN
IDOL.
YOUR JOB IS TO KNOCK THEIR IDOL
OFF BEFORE THEY KNOCK OFF YOURS.
THE FOIRS SCORE FIVE WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THIS WILL MAKE THE
MORNINGS AND AFTERNOONS SWEETER.
>> NO!
>> Jeff: COFFEE, TEA,
BISCUITS, COOKIES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, JEFF TAKING ON
MALCOLM, SQUARING OFF IN ROUND
ONE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> MALCOLM!
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO KNOCK
THEIR HIDEOL OFF YOUR HANDS
BEFORE THEY KNOCK OFF YOURS.
TWO STRONG 50 GUYS, FIGHTING FOR
THIS REWARD.
MALCOLM'S IDOL HIT THE GROUND
FIRST.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> Jeff: JEFF WITH A NICE
SCORE FOR KALABAW.
ARTIS WITH AAN OBVIOUS REACH
ADVANTAGE.
DANA WILL HAVE TO EMPLOY
SOMETHING OTHER THAN FINESSE
AGAINST THIS LONG REACH OF
ARTIS.
TANDANG SCORES.
WE ARE TIED, 1-1.
GO.
NICE LITTLE MATCH GOING HERE.
>> THAT'S IT, THAT'S IT.
USE THAT REACH, BABY.
YOU GOT HER.
>> Jeff: CALL BAH LEADS 2-1.
PENNER VERSUS SKUPIN.
>> YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: SKUPE WIN A NICE MOVE
SCORES FOR TANDANG.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: WE ARE TIED 2-2.
R.C. UP FOR TANDANG, GOING
AGAINST DENISE.
DENISE WOULD LIKE TO PROVE
HERSELF RIGHT HERE.
>> BE CAREFUL, R.C.
>> Jeff: DENISE WITH A NICE
JORK KALABAW SCORES.
KALABAW, 3-2, PLAYING TO FIVE.
CARTER GOING UP FOR KALABAW,
VERSUS PETE FOR TANDANG.
BOTH GUYS CAGEY.
>> COME ON, PETE.
YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: PETE WITH A NICE
MOVE.
TANDANG SCORES!
WE ARE TIED 3-3.
NEXT TWO.
DAWSON VERSUS ABI.
>> YOU GOT IT, BABY.
SEND HER UP DAWSON'S CREEK.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO BE
AGGRESSIVE IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> COME ON, ABI.
>ABI.>> SHE PULLED THE HAIR, SHE
PULLED THE HAIR.
>> Jeff: ABI WITH A NICE MOVE.
TANDANG SCORES AND LEADS 4-3.
SHE WENT FOR MY HAIR.
>> Jeff: WHAT HAPPENED, ABI?
>> SHE WENT FOR A HAIR.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
>> PLAY LIKE A MAN.
>> Jeff:ICAL COMCOULD MAKE
HIMSELF VERY POPULAR BRINGING
HOME THE REWARD FOR TANDANG.
KALABAW NEEDS TO WIN TO STAY
ALIVE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> COME ON, MALCOLM.
>> Jeff: REWARD AND BRAGGING
RIGHTS ON THE LINE RIGHT HERE.
PRETTY EVEN MATCH.
TANDANG WINS REWARD!
MALCOLM, FIRST CHALLENGE ON HIS
NEW TRIBE BRINGS HOME THE
VICTORY FOR TANDANG.
MALCOLM, HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
>> I GOT A TEAM THAT I'M REALLY
EXCITED ABOUT NOW.
AND I'M GOING TO HAVE SOME SUGAR
TONIGHT!
I'M SO HAPPY.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: TANDANG, COME ON
OVER.
GET YOUR REWARD.
>> WE HAVE CHOCOLATE MUFFINS!
>> Jeff: DENISE, FIVE STRAIGHT
CHALLENGES, STILL NO WIN.
>> BUT I'VE GOT A NEW FAMILY,
SO, YOU KNOW, IT MAY BE A LOSS
TODAY BUT TRULY, I HAVE JUST
THIS AWESOME VIBE ABOUT THIS
TRIBE ALREADY.
>> Jeff: KALABAW, GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> I LIKE THIS LADY, BUT I SURE
WOULD HAVE PREFERRED TO HAVE
MALCOLM ON MY TEAM BECAUSE WE
MIGHT HAVE HAD THE COOKIES AND
COFFEE, AND NOW THEY HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE OVER US PHYSICALLY.
>> OH, THIS IS A COOL LITTLE
SPOT.
>> YOU DON'T REALIZE HOW DOWN IN
THE DUMP YOU ARE UNTIL YOU
FINALLY GET A WIN AND THINGS
START GOING YOUR WAY.
I GOT AN IMMUNITY IDOL THIS
MORNING.
I GOT A NEW TRIBE IN THE
AFTERNOON.
I FEEL LIKE I GOT MY SWAG BACK.
>> TANDANG!
>> YA!
>> YEAH!
>> OH!
>> ALL I CAN HOPE FOR IS LOOK
FOR A CRACK AND GET MYSELF
WEDGED IN THERE BECAUSE IT'S THE
EASIEST THING IN THE WORLD TO
SAY HE'S THE ODD GUY, LET'S GET
RID OF HIM.
>> YOU WANT ONE OF THESE
COOKIES.
>> YES, PLEASE.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'RE SO WELCOME.
>> WE WERE ROOTING FOR YOU.
>> YEAH, WE REALLY WANTED YOU.
>> I WANTED TO BE HERE, TOO.
>> MALCOLM HAS BROUGHT WONDERFUL
ENERGY TO OUR TRIBE.
HE'S A GREAT GUY.
HE'S A STRENGTH PHYSICALLY, SO
THAT'S HUGE FOR US IN THE
CHALLENGES.
>> I HAVEN'T EATEN SINCE
YESTERDAY MORNING.
>> OH, ENJOY IT!
YOU SHOULD HAVE ANOTHER ONE.
>> NO I'M FINE.
I SHOULD SO MUCH I FEEL LIKE I
WANT TO DANCE.
I HAVE SO MUCH SUGAR GOING.
>> HE ALSO HAS A GREAT ATTITUDE.
HE'S GOOD-LOOK, HE'S SMART, HE'S
EASY GOING.
SO HE HASN'T BROUGHT ANY KIND OF
NEGATIVE ENERGY INTO THE TRIBE
WHICH IS REALLY GREAT.
>> I THINK I WOULD HAVE FARED
BETTER IF WE GOT DENISE.
>> HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> 24.
>> ME, TOO.
>> YOU KNOW, AT FIRST I THOUGHT
MAYBE I HAD A FIGHTING CHANCE.
MAYBE I CAN GET HIM ON MY SIDE
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE MINUTE I SAW
HIM TALKING TO PETER I KNEW IT
WAS OVER.
YOU KNOW, HAVING THIS NEW PERSON
JOIN AND BE ACCEPTED RIGHT AWAY,
IT SORT OF DOES BRING ME BACK A
LITTLE BIT TO CHILDHOOD BECAUSE
I WAS BULLIED IN SCHOOL.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> ON "SURVIVOR" YOU'RE IN THIS
PLACE WHERE YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE
TO TURN TO.
YOU DON'T HAVE PEOPLE THAT YOU
CAN SORT OF GO AND TALK TO AND
SAY, "THIS IS HOW I'M FEELING.
WHAT SHOULD I BE DOING?
"YOU KNOW.
BUT I DIDN'T STARVE AND HAVE NO
FIRE AND WORK IN THOSE
CHALLENGES TO LET THEM WALK ALL
OVER ME I'M GOING TO FIGHT AND
HOPEFULLY WE DON'T HAVE TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND TIME HAS TO
BE ON MY SIDE AT THIS POINT
BECAUSE I NEED TIME, AND
HOPEFULLY TIME TO FLIRT WITH
MALCOLM.
>> NO PRESSURE, RIGHT?
>> THAT'S FINE.
HEY, WE'VE GOT FIRE.
OH, MY GOD, THANK YOU.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
SUCH A GREAT ADDITION.
THANKS.
>> WHEN I SAW MALCOLM UPWRAP
THAT YELLOW BUFF I WAS ECSTATIC.
I WAS ALWAYS LEERY GETTING RID
OF MIKE BUT NOW WE HAVE ANOTHER
STRONG GUY AND HE'S PROBABLY NOT
AS STUPID.
>> DON'T GO WITH THEM.
MIKE HAS BEEN ANNOYING SINCE DAY
ONE.
STORY AFTER STORY.
YOU'RE TRYING TO MAKE A FIRE, HE
GET HIS HAND IN.
PLUS WE HAVE THE IDOL, SO.
>> OH, YOU DO?
>> THEY DON'T KNOW THAT.
DON'T TELL THEM.
>> OKAY.
SICK.
>> WHENEVER YOU NEED IT, WE'VE
GOT IT.
>> YOU AND ABI HAVE IT?
SICK.
>> INFORMATION IS POWER.
I MIGHT AS WELL GET ALL OF IT AS
I CAN AND IT WASN'T THAT
DIFFICULT FOR PETE TO
IMMEDIATELY SAY, "I HAVE THE
IDOL."
NO ONE KNOWS I HAVE ONE AND IF
PETE IS TELLING ME HE HAWSE ONE
HE MIGHT USE THAT TO SAVE ME OR
SOMETHING WE CAN USE JOINTLY,
NOW BECAUSE OF YOU WE CAN GET
RID OF MIKE.
>> I'M LIKE THE STUD FOOTBALL
PLAYER FROM THE RIFLE.
EVERYONE WANTS TO GET TO KNOW
ME.
EVERYONE IS PULLING ME ASIDE.
I'LL BE YOUR BEST FRIEND.
THOSE GUYS ARE LOSERS.
I WON'T LIE, I'M ENJOYING IT
RIGHT NOW.
>> JUST TO BE IN A NEW FAMILY
AND IN A NEW TRIBE IS GREAT.
>> WELL, WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU GUYS.
AND TRYING TO BLIND BLEND IN
WITH MY NEW FAMILY HERE AND
FIGURE OUT WHAT MY ROLE WILL BE.
I AM REALLY GLAD TO BE PART OF
YOUR TRIBE, I REALLY AM.
WHATEVER I CAN DO TO HELP.
WHATEVER I CAN DO TO PROVE I
HAVE VALUE, EVEN IF IT'S KEEPING
ME AROUND FOR ONE MORE TRIBAL, I
CAN REGROUP.
EVERY STEP IS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
REGROUP AND TURN THINGS AROUND.
>> WE'RE HAPPY TO HAVE YOU.
>>-- I.
>> -- THAT WAS THE BEST THING.
I AM SO HAPPY.
>> SO, MY ALLIANCE CONSISTS OF
DANA, DAWSON, AND MYSELF.
AGAINST THE GUYS.
WE NEED DENISE, LIKE, THAT WAS
THE ONE REASON WHY I WAS HAPPY
WHAT WE GOT A FEMALE BECAUSE WE
HAVE A BETTER CHANCE OF GETTING
DENISE ON OUR SIDE THAN WE DO
GETTING MALCOLM.
FROM HEREON OUT, IT'S MY JOB TO
GET DENISE UNDERNEATH MY ARM.
AS LONG AS WE CAN CONVINCE HER
THAT, HEY OORKT US GIRLS,
HOPEFULLY SHE REALLY WON'T
LISTEN TO THE GUYS
>> GOSH!
WOW!
>> IT'S COLD.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
I'M SOAKED.
>> YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
FEEL GOOD, DANA.
>> I'M NOT OUT OF IT, BUT I'M
TRYING.
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING, AND I
GUESS I JUST HAVE A BAD IMMUNE
SYSTEM, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I JUST CAN'T SHAKE THE COLD.
I AM DIZZY, NAUSEOUS, COMPLETELY
DEHYDRATED.
I STARTED GETTING THIS SHARP
PAIN IN MY STOMACH.
I DON'T KNOW, IT JUST STARTED
GETTING WORSE.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> GET OUT OF THE WAY, GET OUT
OF THE WAY, GET OUT OF THE WAY!
I CAN'T STOP SHAKING.
I CAN'T GET THAT ACHING PAIN OUT
OF MY STOMACH.
I CAN'T HOLD ANYTHING DOWN.
YOU KNOW, BACK HOME, I'M KIND OF
SUPPOSED TO BE TOUGH, BUT YOU'RE
ONLY AS TOUGH AS YOUR BODY, I
THINK, WILL ALLOW YOU TO BE
>> I THINK SHE'LL BE FINE
TOMORROW.
>> WHAT?
SHE'S PROBABLY PUKING HER GUTS
OUT.
DAY 11 SUCKS.
IT'S FREEZING.
AND I'M A BIG, FAT GUY.
YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T REALLY
AFFECT ME THAT MUCH.
BUT DANA'S SICK.
SHE WEIGHS 47 POUNDS OR
SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE'S AS BIG AS MY FINGER, YOU
KNOW.
AND SHE MAY JUST BE SHUTTING
DOWN.
>> COME ON AND GET UNDER THIS
BLANKET, GIRLIE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> WRAP UP IN THAT BLANKET AND
GET WARM BUT YOU GOTTA GET OUT
OF THOSE WET CLOTHES.
TAKE EVERYTHING OFF.
YOU GET NAKED UNDER THAT
BLANKET.
WE'LL WARM YOU UP?
>> ARE YOU IN PAIN?
IS IT YOUR STOMACH?
>> YOU'RE BURNING UP, GIRL.
>> DANA IS IN BAD SHAPE.
SHE CAN BARELY TALK.
YOU WANT TO LAY DOWN IN MY LAP?
I KNOW IT HURTS, HUH?
THIS GIRL IS SHUTTING DOWN.
SHE NEEDED SOME MEDICAL
ATTENTION.
I HEAR A BOAT.
MAYBE THEY'RE COMING NOW.
>> Jeff: IS THAT DANA IN
THERE?
>> YEAH, SHE'S IN THERE.
>> Jeff: OH, MY GOSH!
>> SHE'S GOT A FEVER HEY, DANA,
IT'S JEFF.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK TO JEFF?
>> Jeff: HI, DANA.
WOW.
YOU WERE HIDDEN IN THERE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
GIVE ME AN UPDATE.
>> MY STOMACH.
>> Jeff: LET'S GO.
>> OUT OF NOWHERE JEFF PROBST IS
IN MY CAMP, WHICH IS, YOU KNOW,
TYPICALLY I'D JUMP UP AND DOWN
AND MAYBE JUMP ON HIM, BUT IT
JUST WASN'T GOOD TIMING, YOU
KNOW.
SO HE WAS THERE FOR DANA, AND HE
BROUGHT HER TO SEE MEDICAL.
>> JUST RELAX.
IT'S A BIT UNCOMFORTABLE THERE.
OKAY.
>> Jeff: WHAT ARE YOU SEEING?
>> I'M SEEING AROUND THIS RIGHT
SIDE AND AROUND THE MIDDLE WAS
WHERE SHE WAS HAVING THE MOST
AMOUNT OF PAIN.
>> Jeff: WHAT DOES THE PAIN
FEEL LIKE, DANA?
GIVE ME SOME WAY TO RELATE TO
IT.
>> LIKE A KNIFE.
IT COMES AND IT GOES.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR FIRST
GUESS, JOE?
>> I THINK CERTAINLY HER TUMMY
IS IRRITATED.
WHETHER OR NOT THAT'S FROM AN
INFECTION OR SOME OTHER PROCESS
GOING ON, IT'S HARD TO SAY.
>> Jeff: STOW, CAN YOU TELL
RIGHT NOW IF SHE IS-- WHETHER OR
NOT SHE'S IN PAIN, FORGETTING
THAT, JUST IN TERMS OF HER BEING
ABLE TO CONTINUE, CAN SHE
CONTINUE MEDICALLY?
>> YES, SHE COULD-- WE COULD TRY
IT FOR ANOTHER 12 HOURS.
I THINK WE COULD SEE IF SHE
COULD TRY AND GET SOME MORE
FLUIDS INTO HER, HERSELF, AND WE
COULD TRY AND SEE IF SHE CAN
LAST THAT LONG AND LONGER.
>> Jeff: SO, DANA, THE REASON
I'M BRINGING THIS UP IS,
CLEARLY, YOU'RE UNCOMFORTABLE.
BUT THE ONLY TIME MEDICAL PULLS
ANYBODY FROM THIS GAME IS WHEN
MM DECIDES THEY CANNOT LAST
ANOTHER MOMENT BECAUSE THEIR
LIFE IS IN DANGER.
SO JOE'S SAYING YOU'RE NOT IN A
LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION.
SO NOW IT'S-- IT'S ON YOU.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU WANT TO
DO?
IS THIS SOMETHING YOU'RE READY
TO GIVE UP ON?
>> I GUESS.
YEAH, I CAN'T STAY.
I CAN'T BE OUT HERE SICK ANY
MORE.
I WISH I WASN'T SICK.
>> Jeff: I KNOW YOU'RE IN
PAIN.
YOU'RE PULLING YOURSELF OUT OF
THE GAME?
( CRYING )
DO YOU WANT TO GO AND TELL THE
TRIBE WHAT'S HAPPENING OR DO YOU
WANT ME TO?
HOW DO YOU WANT TO GO OUT?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE RELIEF IN
JUST MOMENTS.
THE PAIN'S GOING TO GO AWAY.
LET'S FINISH THIS ADVENTURE ON
YOUR TERMS, OKAY?
THEY CAN COME OUT HERE.
YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
OKAY.
HANG TIGHT.
COME ON HERE, GUYS.
YOU KNOW BETTER THAN I DO HOW
SHE'S DOING.
BUT SHE WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
GUYS HERSELF.
TELL YOU WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> I TRIED TO HANG.
>> YOU PUSHED YOURSELF THE BEST
YOU COULD AND WE'RE PROUD OF
YOU.
>> Jeff: I WANT TO JUST UPDATE
YOU ON WHAT HAPPENS.
WE DON'T PULL ANYBODY UNLESS
IT'S TRULY LIFE THREATENING, BUT
IT'S CLEAR THAT DANA IS
STRUGGLING SO SHE JUST CAN'T GO
ON ANYMORE, AND SHE WANTED YOU
GUYS TO KNOW.
PENNER, YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS
LIKE.
YOU WENT THROUGH THIS.
>> HORRIBLE, DEVASTATING.
I FELT EXACTLY THE WAY SHE
FEELS.
I TOTALLY EMPATHIZE.
I WAS WEEPING.
I WAS SO FRUSTRATED.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> DON'T BE SORRY.
NOT EVEN FOR A SECOND.
WE'RE ONLY SORRY FOR YOU.
WE'RE SORRY THAT YOU'RE FEELING
SO BAD.
AND KNOW THAT WE-- WE HAVE-- WE
WERE JUST SAYING BACK THERE HOW
MUCH WE LOVE YOU AND RESPECT
YOU.
>> YOU'RE PART OF OUR CAMP.
YOU DID EVERYTHING.
>> AND HOW GREAT IT'S BEEN
GETTING TO KNOW YOU.
>> FEEL BETTER!
>> WE LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
>> THANKS, JEFF.
WE LOVE YOU.
>> TAKE CARE!
>> BYE, BABE.
DANA LEAVING THE GAME SCREWS UP
EVERYTHING.
I'M LITERALLY AT A LOSS UNDER
WORDS BECAUSE THIS COULD NOT
HAVE HAPPENED AT A WORSE TIME.
I MEAN, I LOVE THE GIRL.
IT SUCKS THAT IT HAPPENED.
BUT, LIKE, MY BEST ALLY JUST GOT
TAKEN AWAY BY THE MEDIC.
AND I'M LIKE WHAT THE HELL AM I
GOING TO DO TO SURVIVE?
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
TANDANG GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW KALABAW TRIBE.
DANA FELT SHE WAS TOO SICK TO
CONTINUE.
SHE PULLED HERSELF FROM THE
GAME.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, TANDANG HAS
A ONE-PERSON ADVANTAGE IN THIS
GAME.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAKE BACK THE IDOLS.
THANK YOU.
NO NEED FOR TWO IDOLS ANYMORE.
ONE WILL DO.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ON MY GO,
YOU'LL RACE THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES.
YOU'LL THEN UNTIE KNOTS TO
RELEASE A DRAWBRIDGE.
ONE PERSON WILL CHOP A ROPE,
DROPPING BAMBOO PUZZLE PIECES.
YOU'LL RACE TO FIND THE PEES
WITH LETTERS ON THEM AND USE
THEM TO SOLVE A WORD PHRASE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE GOING
OUT.
TANDANG WINS THEY TAKE A BIG
LEAD IN THIS GAME.
KALABAW HAS A CHANCE TO TIE IT
UP RIGHT HERE.
TANDANG, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
MEMBER, WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SIT
OUT?
ABI, I GOTTA ASK OF ALL THE
CHALLENGES WE'VE HAD, HOW MANY
HAVE YOU PARTICIPATED IN?
>> TWO.
>> Jeff: WOW.
ALL RIGHT, ABI, TAKE A SPOT ON
THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
WOW, CARTER AND SKUPIN QUICKLY
DOWN.
IMPRESSIVE BEGINNING.
GOTTA GET UP AND OVER.
BOTH TRIBES HELPING EACH OTHER
OVER.
GO, TANDANG.
KALABAW OFF TO A SLOW START.
KATY REALLY SLOWING THEM DOWN ON
A VERY EASY PORTION OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
A HUGE SETBACK FOR KALABAW.
TANDANG WITH A BIG LEAD RIGHT
NOW.
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> Jeff: R.C. AND ARTIS
WORKING ON THE ROPE FOR TANDANG.
HERE COMES KALABAW.
KATY ONCE AGAIN LAST ONE OVER.
KATY STRUGGLING.
>> GO!
>> YOU GOT IT, YOU GUYS.
COME ON.
>> Jeff: CARTER AND DENISE
WORKING ON THE ROPES FOR CALL
BAH.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE ROPES UNTIED,
THAT DRAWBRIDGE OF DROP.
GREAT TEAM WORK BY BOTH TRIBES.
TANDANG IS THROUGH THE ROPES UP
TOP.
DENISE HAS ONE HALF OF THE TOP
ROPE FOR KALABAW.
CARTER HAS THE OTHER HALF OF THE
TOP ROPE FOR KALABAW.
KALABAW HAS MADE UP SOME GROUND.
EVERYBODY NOW WORKING ON THE
BOTTOM SET OF ROPES.
NEITHER TRIBE HAS BEEN TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL YET IN THIS GAME.
>> WE GOT IT!
YA!
>> Jeff: TANDANG IS THREW
THEIR DRAW BRIDGE.
KALABAW IS FALL BEHIND.
KEEP MOVING, KALABAW.
MALCOLM CHOPPING THE ROPE FOR
TAN DAIPG.
YOU HAVE TO CHOP ALL THE WAY
THROUGH TO RELEASE THOSE PUZZLE
PIECES.
KALABAW ON THE LAST BIT OF ROPE
TRYING TO GET THROUGH THE
DRAWBRIDGE, STILL SUFFERING FROM
THE BEGINNING WITH KATY.
MALCOLM IS THROUGH THE ROPE!
THEY'VE DROPPED THEIR PUZZLE
PIECES.
>> GOOD!
>> Jeff: KALABAW DROPS THEIR
DRAWBRIDGE.
JEFF GOING TO START CHOPPING ON
THE WOOD FOR KALABAW.
HE'S GOT SOME TIME TO MAKE UP.
TANDANG IS LOOKING FOR EVERY
BAMBOO PIECE THAT HAS A LETTER
ON IT, 19 TOTAL.
JEFF'S SLOWING DOWN NOW.
JEFF GOING TO BAIL OUT, PENNER
GOING TO COME IN TO DO SOME
RELIEF.
PENNER FLYING THROUGH THAT WOOD
NOW.
THE PUZZLE PIECES RELEASED FOR
KALABAW.
TANDANG WITH A BIG HEAD START
AND IT GOES BACK TO THE START OF
THE CHALLENGE, KATY COULD NOT
GET OVER THE MOUND.
IT IS A FIVE-WORD PHRASE.
KALABAW HAS ALL OF THEIR PUZZLE
PIECES.
IT IS PENNER AND DAWSON WORKING
FOR KALABAW, AND LISA AND PETE
WORKING FOR TANDANG.
IF TANDANG WINS, THEY WOULD HAVE
A TWO-PERSON ADVANTAGE IN THE
GAME.
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES WORKING
TOGETHER WELL.
EVERYBODY IN ON THIS CHALLENGE,
EXCEPT FOR ABI SITTING OUT YET
AGAIN.
>> GOT A "Y?"
>> Jeff: TRYING ANOTHER
COMBINATION OF WORDS.
PENNER THINKS HE MIGHT HAVE IT.
>> LIVE TO PLAY.
ANOTHER DAY.
ANOTHER DAY!
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES THINK
THEY HAVE IT.
IT'S A RACE NEW TO SEE WHO CAN
GET IT FIRST.
>> WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT, WE GOT
IT!
>> Jeff: LIVE TO PLAY ANOTHER
DAY.
TANDANG WINS IMMUNITY BY
SECONDS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WE CAME FROM BEHIND ONE MORE
SECOND.
>> Jeff: TANDANG,
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> WHOOO!
>> Jeff: YOU REMAIN UNDEFEATED
IN THIS GAME.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
>> WHOOO!
>> BABY!
>> Jeff: TONIGHT WITH THE
EXCEPTION OF DENISE, THIS WILL
BE A NEW EXPERIENCE FOR KALABAW.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT WHERE ONE
OF THE SIX OF YOU WILL BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> IF KATY HAD BEEN THREE
SECONDS FASTER AND DAWSON HAD
BEEN A LITTLE MORE HELPFUL WITH
THE PUZZLE I THINK WE WOULD HAVE
WON.
AND NOW WE'RE GOING TO BE DOWN
TWO PEOPLE AND THAT GAP AT THIS
STAGE IN THE GAME MAY JUST BE
INSURMOUNTABLE.
>> BIG
TIME.
>> THEIR SIZE ADVANTAGE, THEY
HAVE A MARGIN WE DON'T HAVE.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
I FEEL BAD.
>> WHY?
>> I TOTALLY SUCKED IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
IT'S PRETTY EMBARRASSING TO BE
THE ONE THAT, LIKE, TOTALLY
SCREWED UP EVERYONE.
AND IT'S LIKE I FEEL LIKE EVERY
TIME THEY MAKE A MOAN OR A
GROAN IT'S BECAUSE OF ME.
>> KATY YOU WERE HAVING TROUBLE
ON THAT FIRST ONE.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> NO, YOU WERE HAVING TROUBLE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
>> I SCREWED UP.
THERE'S NOTHING ELSE I CAN
REALLY SAY.
A REALLY CRAPPY PERFORMANCE.
IF I WAS THEM, I'D SAY SEE YOU
LATER, KATY.
THAT SUCTION.
>> NO ONE'S VOTING YOU.
YOU'RE PARANOID.
>> DID YOU NOT SEE ME TODAY?
>> YOU WERE NOT GOOD.
>> I WAS NOT GOOD.
>> I WAS BAD.
>> KATY SUCKED IN THIS CHALLENGE
TODAY.
SHE WAS NO GOOD.
>> I'M EMBARRASSED.
>> I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> YOU WERE NOT GOOD, BUT
ANYWAY, WE HAVE TO MOVE ON FROM
THAT KATY SUCKED.
KATY BLEW IT.
I TOLD KATY SHE SUCKED.
SHE KNOWS SHE SUCKED, BUT
DENISE, SHE'S NORTH PART OF OUR
ORIGINAL TRIBE.
SHE'S ONLY BEEN IN OUR TRIBE FOR
TWO DAYS.
>> I'M A PART OF A TRIBE THAT
HAS LOST AGAIN.
IT'S JUST-- IT'S HEARTBREAKING.
I'M WORRIED.
I HAVEN'T HAD 13 DAYS TO BOND
WITH THESE GUYS.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE GOING TO
GO LOYALTY OR THEY'RE GOING TO
GO LOGIC.
>> I DIDN'T COME OUT HERE TO
KEEP VISITING JEFF AT TRIBAL.
I MEAN, TRULY--
>> THAT'S THING.
THERE'S AN ALLIANCE OF THREE
WHERE I'M IN.
WE HAVE TO KNOW IF YOU'RE ON OUR
SIDE.
>> I WANT TO BE ON YOUR GUYS'
>> THE THING IS, IF YOU'RE WITH
US, THEN YOU'RE THE FOURTH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> GOT IT.
>> WE NEED THEM IN, AND RIGHT
NOW IT COMES DOWN TO, YOU KNOW,
WHO IS GOING TO HOLD THE MOST
VALUE IN THE CHALLENGES FOR US.
DENISE IS STRONGER THAN DAWSON
AND KATY.
I THINK SHE'S PHYSICAL AND SHE'S
MENTAL.
I THINK SHE'S GOT SOME PRETTY
GOOD SMART ON HER.
>> I THINK I GOT DENISE ON OUR
SIDE.
>> SHE'S WITH US THREE.
>> PERFECT.
>> SO WE'VE GOT FOUR.
>> DENISE?
WE'RE GREAT.
>> SHE'S GREAT.
THERE ARE REALLY THREE OPTIONS
AT THIS POINT.
DENISE, KATY, OR DAWSON.
BUT I CAN'T SEE GETTING RID OF
DENISE NOW.
SHE'S A HELL OF A COMPETITOR.
SHE WAS RIGHT IN IT TO WIN IT
TODAY.
NO WAY COULD WE POINT AT HER AND
SAY SHE'S THE ONE WHO CAUSED US
THIS CHALLENGE.
SO IT'S KATY OUR DAWSON.
DAWSON, I NEED YOU TO FIND SOME
MORE WOOD.
>> OKAY.
>> ARE WE ALONE?
>> BARELY ALONE.
>> IT'S EITHER KATY OR DAWSON.
>> I MEAN, I KIND OF WISH IT WAS
KATY.
KATY JUST LOOKS CHECKED OUT TO
ME.
EVEN NOW, SHE'S JUST WALKING
AROUND THE BEACH.
>> WE LOST DAWSON.
SHE HAD PUZZLES IN HER HAND AND
YOU WERE TRYING TO GET THEM AND
SHE WASN'T EVEN GIVING THEM TO
YOU.
I'M FIEWMED.
>> I'M WILLING TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I'D JUST LIKE TO-- I DON'T KNOW.
KATY DID NOT PERFORM WELL TODAY.
SHE PERFORMED POORLY.
AND I CAN'T SAY THAT THAT'S WHAT
COST US THE CHALLENGE.
BUT IT DIDN'T HELP.
BUT BEFORE TODAY, DAWSON IS JUST
BEEN THE WEAKEST MEMBER OF THE
TRIBE.
I DON'T THINK SHE PERFORMED
PARTICULARLY WELL TODAY.
STAFDISASTROUSLY.
IT'S A BIG CHOICE, ACTUALLY.
>> MAYBE I SHOULD DATE AN
ATHLETE.
>> WHAT DO YOU CONSIDER AN
ATHLETE?
>> FOOTBALL, BASKETBALL, THEN I
GUESS AT THE END MAYBE BASEBALL.
I KNOW JEFF IS FROM A
PROFESSIONAL ATHLETE, AND AS FAR
AS I KNOW, I'M THE ONLY PERSON
WHO KNOWS.
SO I ENJOE GETTING INTO HIS MIND
AND MAKING HIM UNCOMFORTABLE.
THERE'S TOO MUCH STANDING
AROUND.
IT'S, LIKE, A WHOLE BUNCH OF
GROWN GUYS JUST LIKE-- IT'S A
LOT OF FUN TO MAKE HIM SQUIRM.
AND IT'S A LOT OF FUN TO-- I
DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE KIND OF GOT,
LIKE, A LITTLE MOUSE THAT
DOESN'T KNOW IT'S IN A CORNER,
AND I'M LIKE PLAYING WITH IT.
AND I'M GOING TO SNAP ON IT.
FOOTBALL IS BETTER THAN
BASEBALL.
>> DAWSON STARTS TALKING A LOT
OF SPORTS, SO I'M WALKING ON
EGGSHELLS RIGHT NOW BECAUSE
RIGHT NOW I'M HAVING A GOOD TIME
WITH THESE PEOPLE BEING NORMAL,
AND I AM NORMAL.
THAT'S WHAT I AM.
I USED TO BE A BALL PLAYER.
NO PROBLEM ABOUT IT.
I'M HERE JUST LIKE THEM DOING
THE SAME THING.
IF THEY PUT TWO AND TWO TOGETHER
I'M IN TROUBLE.
TONIGHT'S VOTE COULD BE BASED ON
A VALUE FOR WINNING CHALLENGES
IN OUR TRIBE.
YOU KNOW, IT MAY BE KATY.
IT MAY BE DAWSON.
>> LET'S JUST GET THIS DONE
RIGHT NOW.
IS IT KATY OR IS IT HER?
>> DAWSON KNOWS MY HISTORY AS AN
ATHLETE AND THE BEST SCENARIO
MIGHT BE JUST TO VOTE HER
OUT.
>> FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T
HAVE A TORCH APPROACH THE FLAME
AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
AND AS LONG AS YOU HAVE FIRE,
YOU ARE STILL IN THIS GAME, AND
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
AND, UNFORTUNATELY, TONIGHT,
THAT WILL BE THE CASE FOR ONE OF
YOU.
DAWSON, HOW DID DANA LEAVING
IMPACT THIS TRIBE?
>> DANA LEAVING HIT US HARDER
THAN THE RAIN EVER COULD.
SHE WAS ONE OF THE STRONGEST
PEOPLE I'VE EVER MET.
SEEING HER FALL AND GET SO WEAK
AND FEEL SO HELPLESS THAT SHE'S
JUST BANGING HER FIST ON THE
GROUND BECAUSE SHE WANTS TO STAY
BUT PHYSICALLY SHE CAN'T, THAT
HIT US VERY HARD.
>> Jeff: PENNER, IN THREE DAYS
YOU GO FROM BEING UNDEFEATED AND
NOW YOU'RE DOWN TWO.
>> YEAH, IT'S TERRIBLE.
I MEAN IT'S JUST BAD LUCK.
SOMEBODY ON THEIR TRIBE COULD
HAVE GOTTEN SICK AND WE COULD BE
IN A COMPLETELY OPPOSITE PLACE.
AND, HONESTLY, I BELIEVE IF DANA
WERE HEALTHY AND WITH US TODAY
WE WOULD HAVE WON THAT
CHALLENGE.
SO LOSING HER WAS DEVASTATING TO
US.
>> Jeff: KATIE, AT TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, MISERABLE START FOR
THE TRIBE ON YOUR SHOULDERS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I FEEL LIKE THE BIGGEST IDIOT IN
THE WORLD.
I'M NOT MAKING EXCUSES FOR
MYSELF AT ALL, BECAUSE,
OBVIOUSLY, THESE PEOPLE COULD DO
IT.
SO, REALLY, ALL I CAN DO IS HOPE
THAT THEY BELIEVE IN ME AND
THEY'VE SEEN ME COMPETE IN OTHER
CHALLENGES AND THEY KNOW THAT I
AM CAPABLE, AND I AM WORTHY TO
STAY HERE.
>> Jeff: PENNER, WOULD IT BE
FAIR TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT WHO
LET YOU DOWN AT THE CHALLENGE?
>> IF IT'S JUST BASED ON THE
TODAY'S PERFORMANCE, YES, THAT
WOULD BE AN EASY VOTE.
>> Jeff: DAWSON, DENISE IS THE
NEWEST MEMBER ON THIS TRIBE, BUT
SHE SEEMS TO BE A PRETTY WORTHY
COMPETITOR.
ARGUMENT FOR HER STAYING AND
SOMEONE ELSE GOING?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE NEED EVERY COMPETITOR WE CAN
GET OUR HANDS ON, AND NOW WE'RE
HERE, AND IT'S DEFINITELY
BITTERSWEET.
YOU KNOW, WE LOVE TO SEE YOU,
BUT IT SUCKS HAVING TO VOTE
SOMEONE OUT.
>> Jeff: DAWSON, WHY KEEP YOU?
>> I TRY TO KEEP THE SPIRIT OF
THE CAMP UP.
YOU KNOW, I TRY TO BE OPTIMISTIC
AND EMPOWERING, BEING POSITIVE
IN THIS WEATHER IN 13 DAYS OF
RAIN, THAT GOES PRETTY FAR.
>> Jeff: JEFF, WHAT ARE THE
BIGGEST FACTORS FOR YOU THAT
YOU'RE GOING TO BASE YOUR VOTE
ON TONIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK WE LOOK AT
ALL WEAK LINKS IN OUR TRIBE.
WE LOOK AT PEOPLE WORKING AROUND
THE CAMP.
WE LOOK AT VALUE GOING FORWARD,
LOYALTY.
WE LOOK AT CHALLENGES.
WE NEED TO WIN CHALLENGES TO
KEEP OUR NUMBERS UP.
SO THAT'S A FACTOR IN OUR
DECISION TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FOR THE
FIRST TIME, KALABAW, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
KATIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, DENISE.
DAWSON.
ONE VOTE DENISE, ONE VOTE
THAT'S THREE VOTES DAWSON, ONE
VOTE DENISE.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES, DAWSON.
WOW.
>> Jeff: THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DAWSON, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
FIRST BLINDSIDE.
BUT MOREALLY, YOU ARE NOW DOWN
TWO TRIBE MEMBERS IN A GAME ALL
ABOUT NUMBERS.
THIS TRIBE HAS GOT TO GET A WIN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
IN A WAR BETWEEN TANDANG AND
KALABAW--
>> COME ON, GUYS, DIG DEEP!
>> Jeff: IT'S GETTING PHYSICAL
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
EVERYONE PLAYS DIRTY.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR WHAT I
HAVE TO SAY.
>> Jeff: AND THE GAME GETS
PERSONAL.
>> YOU CAN KEEP ALL THAT MESS TO
YOURSELF.
>> ALL RIGHT, CALM DOWN.
>> Jeff: I'M PRETTY SURE THIS
IS UNPRECEDENTED.
>> I COULD HAVE BLOWN UP HIS
SPOT, BUT MAYBE HE COULD BE ONE
OF THOSE, YOU KNOW, MILLIONAIRES
WHO ACTUALLY COME ON THE SHOW
AND WIN.
IF HE WINS, HE OWES ME SO BIG!
I WANT A MOTORCYCLE AND A SIDE
CAR, AND A PINK GUN.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT FROM JEFF