>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR".
>> 3 OF US ARE VOTING
FOR PHILLIP.
>> FOR WEEKS, STEALTH R US HAD
CONTROL OF THE GAME WHILE THE
THREE AMIGOS PULLED OFF A
SHOCKING MOVE.
>> THIS IS THE OTHER IDOL I'VE
BEEN HANGING ON TO.
I'M GIVING IT TO EDDIE.
>> Jeff: USING TWO IDOLS TO
BLIND SIDE PHILLIP.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: WITH PHILLIP GONE THEY
HOPED STEALTH R US WOULD FALL
APART.
BUT THEY WERE WRONG.
>> FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
MALCOLM, YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH MALCOLM AND REYNOLD
WENT HOME BACK TO BACK WE'RE
DOWN TO ONE AMIGO LEFT.
>> ERIK WINS IMMUNITY!
I HAVE A ERIK WON THE LAST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IT SEEMED
OBVIOUS EDDIE WOULD BE THE NEXT
ONE VOTED OUT BUT INSTEAD THE
GAME CHANGED AGAIN AND THE
MAJORITY ALLIANCE BEGAN TO
TARGET EACH OTHER.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK SHOULD GO
HOME?
BRENDA OR DAWN?
>> I THINK TODAY IS THE
BEGINNING OF THE END FOR
ALLIANCE OF SIX.
>> Jeff: AT A SURPRISING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE
TURNED ON EACH OTHER.
>> ANDREA?
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: AND WITH AN IDOL IN HER
POCKET, ANDREA WAS THE FIRST OF
THE SIX TO BE BLINDSIDED.
ANDREA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SIX ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL ANDREA
WAS THE ONE WHO WOUND UP GOING
HOME, TAKING WITH HER THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IF NOW THAT SHE'S GONE, I ALMOST
FEEL LIKE THAT DOORS ARE CLOSED
AND I THINK I'M PRETTY MUCH A
SITTING DUCK TARGET FOR THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WELL, AT LEAST WE KNOW WE'RE
VOTING SOMEBODY OUT EVERY NIGHT
NOW.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> WE'LL GET RID OF THREE MORE
PEOPLE IN FIVE DAYS.
I THINK I'M NEXT.
>> YEAH, BUT IF YOU WIN IMMUNITY
YOU WON'T BE NEXT.
>> POTENTIALLY YOU.
>> REALLY.
>> I WOULD SAY SO.
>> IS THAT WHO YOU WOULD BE
VOTING FOR OR WHO YOU'RE SAYING
THE GROUP WOULD BE VOTING FOR?
>> THE GROUP WOULD BE VOTING
FOR.
>> I ALWAYS THOUGHT I'M THE
WORTHLESS ANNOYING TWERP WHO'S
NOT GOING TO WIN IN CHALLENGES
BUT NOW I'M TAKING A STEP BACK
AND THINKING TO MYSELF "CAN I
GET TO THE END OF THIS GAME OR
DO I HAVE AN EXPIRATION DATE
THAT'S RAPIDLY APPROACHING"?
>> IF EDDIE WINS, WHO GOES NEXT?
>> I THINK IT SHOULD BE COCHRAN.
>> IS ERIK ON BOARD WITH TAKING
-- COCHRAN GOING OR DO YOU FEEL
LIKE HE'S GOING TO BE --
>> I'M PRETTY SURE, YEAH.
>> OKAY.
I WOKE UP FEELING GOOD ABOUT
BEING LOCKED WITH COCHRAN AND
SHERI BUT NOW I HAVE BRENDA AND
ERIK SAYING "WE'LL WORK WITH YOU
AT THE END" SO I'M THINKING
MAYBE THAT GUARANTEES ME FINAL
THREE IF I GO WITH THEM.
BUT THEN THAT BRAEBS MY
AGREEMENT WITH COCHRAN AND I'M
KNOWING THAT THEY WANT TO TARGET
HIM.
>> I FEEL LIKE I COULDN'T TRUST
YOU AND THAT VOTE WAS REALLY
HARD FOR ME.
BUT I KNOW HE'S A BIG THREAT TO
WIN THE GAME.
>> YEAH.
>> THE GOOD THING HERE IS THAT I
HAVE OPTIONS AND I'M GOING TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR HIT IN THE
END AND PROVED TO PEOPLE THAT I
PLAYED A GAME THAT WAS WORTH A
MILLION DOLLARS.
>> THIS IS WHAT YOUR 70th DAY
PLAYING THE GAME, SNASHG
>> 70th DAY ON "SURVIVOR".
>> WHOA!
>> CRAZINESS.
I SHOULD BE HAPPY TODAY BUT I'M
NOT.
I SHOULD BE REALLY, REALLY HAPPY
AND CONTENT BUT THIS HAS BEEN
ONE OF THE HARDEST DAYS YET FOR
WHATEVER REASON.
I HAVE TO HAVE FOOD.
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN PRISON RIGHT
NOW.
I FEEL LIKE THERE'S JUST SO MUCH
TIME, IT'S STRETCHED OUT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M TRAPPED HERE AND
IT'S HORRIBLE.
I MEAN, THERE'S NOTHING TO BE
TALKED ABOUT.
THERE'S NOTHING TO BE SAID.
THERE'S NOTHING TO BE DONE.
I'M MISERABLE HERE.
THIS IS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
PRISON I'VE EVER BEEN IN IN MY
LIFE.
THESE DAYS ARE KILLING ME.
THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY KILLING ME.
>> SO ANNOYING TO SEE, LIKE,
COCONUTS IN THE TREE AND YOU
CAN'T GET THEM.
I'M SO HUNGRY FOR THOSE
COCONUTS.
I THINK I CAN CLIMB THAT TREE IF
I TAKE MY TIME.
I THINK I CAN CLIMB IT.
TO SHAKE UP THE DAY I WAS
THINKING I'LL CRIME A COCONUT
TREE TO GET COCONUTS.
I'M SUPER HUNGRY AND THESE
COCONUTS HAVE BEEN LAUGHING AT
ME SINCE DAY THREE.
>> THAT'S TOO TALL, ERIK, THAT'S
A REALLY HIGH COCONUT TREE.
>> PRETTY HIGH, YEAH.
AS I'M CLIMBING THE TREE I'M
THINKING "YOU COULD FALL OUT OF
THE TREE AND BREAK YOUR LEG AND
THEN YOU'LL LEAVE THE GAME AND
YOU'LL SEE MORE COCONUTS."
NO ONE WOULD JUDGE ME, NO ONE
WOULD SAY "HEY, YOU TRIED YOUR
BEST, IT WAS JUST AN ACCIDENT."
BUT I'M TRYING TO DEFEAT MYSELF
AT THIS POINT.
IT'S IN MY HEAD.
AND THAT SCARES THE HELL OUT OF
ME BECAUSE THAT'S NOT WHAT I
WANT TO TO DO.
>> GOOD JOB, ERIK.
NOT FROM THERE, NOT YET.
>> IT'S STILL ABOUT TEN FEET.
>> 12 FEET.
NOT YET.
(APPLAUSE)
NO MORE.
>> NO COCONUTS, THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
>> MAN.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH, I'M FINE.
>> THAT'S THE HIGHEST I'VE SEEN
YOU CLIMB.
>> DAMN IT!
>> I KNOW.
>> OOH, ALL RIGHT.
HEY, GUYS!
YEAH?
>> GATHER AROUND.
>> OH, MY GOD!
NO!
>> WHAT?
>> D.W.I.S COME OVER HERE.
>> NO WAY!
>> COME ON OVER HERE.
>> SPRINT EQUALS LOVE, NOW GO TO
GALLERY TO SEE WHAT YOU ARE
PLAYING FOR.
VIDEO LETTERS.
NO WAY.
>> HI, IT'S DADDY!
WE HAVE TRAVELED OVER 30 HOURS
TO GET HERE.
WE MISS YOU SO, SO, SO VERY
MUCH.
>> THE ONE PERSON I WANT TO HUG
THE MOST I'M ACTUALLY GOING TO
BE ABLE TO HUG OUT HERE-- MY
DAD.
HE'S THE GUY WHO TOLD ME TO BE
HUMBLE AND I'VE BEEN DOING THAT
THIS WHOLE GAME, YOU KNOW?
>> HEY, I'M HERE ON THE ISLAND.
I MISS YOU SO MUCH.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
THIS IS OUR 21st ANNIVERSARY.
IT'S AMAZING.
YOU'VE OUTDONE ME ONCE AGAIN BY
BRINGING ME ALL THE WAY OUT TO
THE PHILIPPINES FOR OUR
ANNIVERSARY.
I LOVE BEING MARRIED TO YOU, I'M
GRATEFUL EVERYDAY.
>> HEY, SWEETHEART, I'M HERE ON
THE ISLAND.
THE KIDS ARE DOING GREAT.
PARKER GOT HIS HAIR CUT YOU
WON'T RECOGNIZE HIM.
I LOVE YOU AND I'LL SEE YOU REAL
SOON.
>> COCHRAN, IT'S BEEN AN
AGONIZING FEW WEEKS LEADING UP
TO THIS DAY.
HOPE YOU'VE BEEN USING LOTS OF
SUNSCREEN ON YOUR PRECIOUS SILKY
WHITE SKIN.
>> HEY!
I'M HERE!
LISTEN, I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU,
VERY PROUD OF EVERYTHING YOU'RE
DOING.
I DON'T KNOW WHY GOD GAVE ME THE
OPPORTUNITY TO BE YOUR FATHER
BUT I'LL TAKE IT.
I'LL TAKE IT.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> HEY, ERIK, IT'S YOUR BROTHER.
>> MY BROTHER!
>> THE WEATHER COULDN'T BE
BETTER.
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
I HOPE YOU'RE HAVING A GOOD TIME
AND YOU'RE STILL THERE, YOU'RE
DOING REALLY WELL.
>> MY BROTHER'S VIDEO, I WAS AT
THE END OF MY ROPE AND I'M NOT
THERE ANYMORE.
I'M RIGHT BACK IN IT.
I'M READY TO FIGHT.
IT TOTALLY REINVIGORATED ME.
EVERYTHING IS TURNED AROUND.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I'M 100% NOW.
I'VE NOT BEEN HERE FOR THIS LONG
TO GO HOME WITH NOTHING.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
THIS MORNING IN TREEMAIL YOU
RECEIVED A AN EVO L.T.D. FROM
SPRINT.
WHO HAS IT?
ERIK?
>> I MADE A FEW CALLS.
>> Jeff: GOOD.
ON THIS SPRINT PHONE WERE
AUTHENTIC VIDEO MESSAGES FROM
YOUR LOVED ONES.
AFTER 35 DAYS, VERY FEW THINGS
CAN RIVAL AL LOVED ONE'S MESSAGE
ON A SPRINT PHONE OTHER THAN,
PERHAPS, THE REAL THING.
BRENDA, HERE'S YOUR DAD RAYMOND.
(APPLAUSE)
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> DADDY, YOU GAVE ME THE BEST,
BEST ADVICE.
THE BEST.
>> I DID?
>> YOU TOLD ME TO BE HUMBLE AND
I'VE BEEN BEING SO HUMBLE
BECAUSE OF YOU.
I THINK OF YOU EVERY NIGHT.
EVERY NIGHT.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, I JUST BROKE.
26 SEASONS AND I'VE NEVER CRIED
AT A LOVED ONE.
YOU GOT ME!
>> I'M SO HAPPY!
I'M SO HAPPY.
>> Jeff: RAYMOND, TAKE YOUR SPOT
OVER HERE, BRENDA, YOU CAN HEAD
BACK.
ERIK, YOU READY FOR SOME LOVE?
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: HERE'S YOUR BROTHER
RICHARD.
>> BROTHER!
>> OH, YES!
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE BIGGER
THAN ME!
>> YOU'RE SO MUCH SMALLER THAN I
AM.
>> HOLY CRAP!
>> Jeff: SHERRI, HERE'S YOUR
HUSBAND JARED.
>> OH, SHERRI!
>> HI, BABE!
OH, GOD!
I JUST WANT YOU TO HOLD ME!
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, HERE'S YOUR
MOM ARLENE.
>> OH!
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SORRY I SMELL.
>> Jeff: EDDIE, LET'S GET TO IT.
HERE'S YOUR POP, ALSO NAMED ED.
>> YES, BIG ED.
>> OH, MY GOD!
YOU'RE THE HAIRIEST MAN ALIVE!
I LOVE YOU!
>> Jeff: THAT'S A HUG RIGHT
THERE.
DAWN, IS THERE ANYBODY OTHER
THAN YOUR HUSBAND YOU'D WANT TO
BE HERE?
>> NO!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S BRING
HIM OUT, HERE'S YOUR HUSBAND OF
21 YEARS, JAMES.
>> JAMES!
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE HERE!
>> ALL THE KIDS ARE GREAT.
>> I SAW THE LETTER BUT I DIDN'T
KNOW.
>> THEY'RE ALL DOING GREAT.
(APPLAUSE)
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ARE YOU
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU ARE GOING TO COMPETE WITH
YOUR LOVED ONES.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU AND
YOUR LOVED ONES WILL SPIN AROUND
IN CIRCLES UNCREW AGO RAIL.
ONCE YOU'VE UNSCREWED ALL THREE
RAILS YOU WILL THEN ATTEMPT TO
TOSS BOLOS ON TO THOSE RAILS.
THE FIRST PAIR TO LAND THREE
BOLOS WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THE WINNING PAIR WILL
GO BACK TO CAMP WHERE JUST
OFFSHORE WE HAVE SET UP A
FLOATING BACKYARD BARBECUE WITH
EVERYTHING YOU WOULD EXPECT AT A
BARBECUE: STEAK, BURGERS, BEER,
APPLE PIE.
>> APPLE PIE!
OH, GOD!
>> Jeff: I KNOW IT'S WORTH
PLAYING FOR.
WE'LL DRAW SPOTS AND GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR A NICE REWARD AND TIME WITH
YOUR LOVED ONES, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
>> RUN!
(LAUGHING SGLCHLD OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE ONLY AS FAST AS
YOUR SLOWEST MEMBER.
>> CAN YOU GO FASTER?
ERIK AND HIS BROTHER FLYING
THROUGH IT.
EVERYBODY DOING A GOOD JOB.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO GET
DIZZY, THAT'S THE POINT.
>> COME ON, OKAY.
GO, GO.
>> Jeff: ERIK AND HIS BROTHER
HAVE THE FIRST RAIL, BRENDA AND
HER DAD HAVE THEIR FIRST RAIL.
HERE COMES ED AND EDDIE.
THERE GOES DAWN AND SHERRI WITH
THEIRS.
EVERYBODY HAS TO COMPENSATE FOR
THEIR LOVED ONE.
THEY'RE NOT USED TO THIS.
IT'S VERY HOT AS WELL.
ARLENE ALREADY SLOWING DOWN.
>> DON'T SAY ANYTHING ABOUT MY
MOM, JEFF.
>> Jeff: HOW OLD ARE YOU,
ARLENE?
>> SHE'S ABOUT TO TURN 54 IN A
FEW WEEKS.
>> Jeff: YOU LOOK GOOD, WOMAN,
BUT KEEP MOVING!
>> THANKS, I KNOW!
>> Jeff: BRENDA AND RAYMOND HAVE
THEIR SECOND RAIL.
DAD GOES DOWN, TAKES A HARD
TUMBLE.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR."
ERIK AND HIS BROTHER HAVE THEIR
SECOND RAIL.
THERE'S THE SECOND RAIL FOR JACK
AND BRENDA.
HERE COMES SHERRI AND JARED.
WE'VE GOT A RACE GOING THERE.
DAWN HAS HER SECOND RAIL.
HERE COMES ED AND EDDIE.
HERE COMES COCHRAN AND HIS MOM.
ERIK AND HIS BROTHER HAVE THEIR
THIRD RAIL.
HERE COMES BRENDA AND HER DAD.
START WORKING ON THOSE KNOTS.
>> SO PROUD OF YOU DADDY.
>> WAS THE FLIGHT OVER HORRIBLE?
>> YEAH, BUT IT WAS FINE.
>> Jeff: SHERRI AND JARED HAVE
THEIR THIRD RAIL.
ERIK HAS HIS KNOTS FREE.
>> LOVE YOU, BABE.
>> LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
NO MORE RUNNING AFTER THIS.
>> Jeff: ERIK'S BROTHER RICHARD
HITS THE FIRST BOLO, THEY'VE
LANDED ONE.
>> THEY GOT ONE.
>> Jeff: JARED AND SHERRI GOING
START TOSSING BOLOS.
YOU NEED TO LAND THREE.
BRENDA TOSSING NOW.
BRENDA HAS ONE, ERIK HAS ONE.
SHERRI AND JARED HAVE THEIR
FIRST.
DAVE HAS ONE FOR DAWN.
ED AND EDDIE SCORE THEIR FIRST!
JARED SCORES A SECOND.
BRENDA SCORES A SECOND.
BRENDA TRYING TO WIN IT RIGHT
HERE.
>> DON'T MISS!
>> Jeff: JUST MISSES.
DAVE SCORES A SECOND.
IT'S A SHOWDOWN.
IT'S BRENDA, JOHN, AND SHERRI.
WHO'S GOING TO GET IT FIRST?
DAVE'S TANGLED.
>> LET ME TRY, DADDY.
>> Jeff: RAYMOND HITS IT!
BRENDA AND RAYMOND WIN REWARD!
>> I LOVE YOU!
>> THIS IS SO GOOD!
YOU DID SO GOOD.
BRENDA, RAYMOND, COME ON OVER.
ALL RIGHT, BRENDA, HERE'S HOW
IT'S GOING TO WORK.
YOU GO BACK TO CAMP WHERE 50
YARDS OFFSHORE WE HAVE A
FLOATING BACKYARD BARBECUE.
CHOOSE ONE OTHER SURVIVOR AND
THEIR LOVED ONE TO JOIN YOU.
>> BRENDA, PLEASE!
>> I'M PICKING DAWN.
I TAKING DAWN FOR SO MANY
REASONS.
>> Jeff: DAWN NOT EVEN MESSING
AROUND.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH!
>> Jeff: LET ME COMPLICATE
THINGS FOR YOU.
HERE'S ANOTHER EVO L.T.E. FROM
SPRINT.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS.
>> HEY, BRENDA, I'M HERE, TOO,
AND I'VE GOT MORE LOVE FOR
EVERYONE!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> YOUR SECOND LOVED ONES ARE
HERE.
>> NO WAY!
>> NO, THEY'RE NOT!
>> Jeff: FIRST TIME IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY TWO LOVED
ONES FOR EVERYBODY.
ARLENE, WHO'S OUT HERE WITH YOU?
>> COCHRAN'S DAD.
>> Jeff: JARED, WHO CAME OUT
WITH YOU.
>> PARKER, OUR OLDEST SON.
>> OH, SHERRI!
SFL.
>> Jeff: BROUGHT SHERRI
LITERALLY TO HER KNEES.
>> OH, GOD!
>> Jeff: RICHARD, WHO CAME OUT
HERE WITH YOU.
>> OUR THIRD BROTHER, LAST PIECE
OF THE PUZZLE.
>> ED, WHO CAME OUT HERE WITH
YOU.
>> MY WIFE, EDDIE'S MOM.
>> Jeff: DAVE, WHO CAME OUT WITH
YOU.
>> WHITNEY, DAWN'S BEST FRIEND.
>> OH, THAT'S NUTS!
>> Jeff: AND WHO CAME OUT WITH
YOU?
>> MY SISTER!
>> Jeff: HERE'S YOUR DILIMA
MACHLT YOU CAN CHOOSE ONE OTHER
SURVIVOR AND THEIR LOVED ONE OR
YOU CAN GIVE UP YOUR LOVE AND
THE LOVE YOU JUST TEASED DAWN
WITH AND THE OTHER FOUR
REMAINING SURVIVORS AND THEIR
LOVED ONES WILL ENJOY THE
BARBECUE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, IT'S A BIG
DECISION.
IT'S LOVE FOR YOU AND DAWN OR
LOVE FOR EVERYONE ELSE.
YOU CAN GIVE UP A CHANCE TO BOND
AND HAVE THIS EXPERIENCE WITH
YOUR SISTER AND YOU CAN TAKE
AWAY WHAT YOU JUST PROMISED DAWN
WHAT'S THE BEST MOVE VERSUS A
ONCE IN A LIFETIME EXPERIENCE.
>> THIS GAME IS CRAZY.
>> OF COURSE I'M GOING TO GIVE
IT TO THEM.
>> OH, YES!
BRENDA, THANK YOU SO MUCH!
>> OH, BRENDA!
>> THE I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
A FEW MORE DAYS.
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
JUST OFFSHORE BEAUTIFUL BARBECUE
WHERE YOUR FOUR LOVED ONES WILL
BE WAITING FOR YOU.
YOU HAVE TO EVO L.T.D. THAT YOU
CAN GIVE TO WHOEVER YOU WANT TO
RECORD ONCE IN A LIFETIME
MEMORIES.
RIGHT NOW, YOU TWO, BRENDA AND
DAWN YOU CAN SAY GOOD-BYE TO
YOUR LOVED ONES.
>> BYE, DADDY.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> THANK YOU, I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR
STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP, ENJOY
YOUR AFTERNOON OF LOVE.
>> SUMMER OF 2000 I'M 13 YEARS
OLD SITTING ON THE COUCH AT HOME
WITH MY MOM WATCHING "SURVIVOR."
OVER THE NEXT 13 YEARS STILL
BEEN WATCHING IT, NEVER MISSED
AN EPISODE.
I WENT THROUGH MY FIRST KISS,
PUBERTY, A LITTLE BIT MORE THAN
THAT AND THIS IS THE CULMINATION
OF 13 YEARS OF LOVING THIS AND
LOVING THIS WITH SOMEBODY I LOVE
AND GETTING TO SHARE THIS NIGHT
WITH SOMEBODY I LOVE.
YOU CAN'T BEAT IT.
>> LOOK AT YOU!
>> EDDIE'S DONE GREAT IN THE
GAME SO FAR BUT HE LOOKED SO
THIN.
HE WAS THIN WHEN HE LEFT SO I
CAN'T BELIEVE HOW THIN HE IS
NOW.
HE TOLD ME HE'D LOST SOMETHING
LIKE 22 POUNDS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET HIM HOME AND
FATTEN HIM UP.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
WHEN MY HUSBAND CAME AROUND THE
CORNER AT THE CHALLENGE I GOT
WEAK IN THE KNEES AND IT TOOK MY
BREATH AWAY.
AND WHEN I HEARD THAT PARKER WAS
HERE ON THE ISLAND IT WAS --
THAT'S WHAT I GAVE BIRTH TO HIM
AND I PUT HIM IN MY ARMS.
I WANTED THAT FEELING AGAIN, TO
HOLD HIM.
>> OH, MY GOD, DRINKS.
>> HAMBURGERS.
>> HAVE SOME BURGERS.
>> YOU WANT A DRINK OR ANYTHING?
>> HOW'S IT SNAIS
>> IT'S PLEASANT, JUST EAT.
>> MY DAD'S A NEUROLOGIST, KIND
OF A BOOKISH GUY, HE'S WEARING
SUNGLASSES ALL OF A SUDDEN AND
WORKING THE GRILL LIKE AN OLD
PRO.
I THINK HE HAS THIS ACT LIKE A
COOL DUDE WHEN HE'S ANYTHING
BUT.
HE'S BASICALLY ME IN 40 YEARS.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S GONE
HOLLYWOOD OR WHAT'S GOING ON BUT
HE'S FLIPPING BURGERS AND LIKE
SINCE WHEN ARE WE DOING THAT,
DAD?
>> COME ON IN!
>> I CAN GET A PICTURE WITH
COCHRAN.
THIS IS A BIG DEAL FOR ME.
(LAUGHS)
>> I'M EXHAUSTED, I'M HUNGRY.
IT'S BREAKING ME DOWN.
I FEEL LIKE I'M BEYOND RATIONAL
THINKING.
I'M JUST BEAT.
>> WE LOVE YOU!
>> YOU'RE NOT MISSING MUCH.
IT'S JUST OKAY!
THANK YOU, BRENDA!
>> I FEEL LIKE BRENDA EARNED ALL
THE GOOD FAVOR TODAY BECAUSE
SHE'S THE ONE THAT GIFTED
EVERYBODY.
SOMEHOW I FEEL LIKE I'M JUST
LOST.
AND THE FACT THAT I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO SPEND CAMP TONIGHT WITH
PEOPLE WHO ARE FULL AND SEEING
THEIR LOVED ONES FOR WHOLE
AFTERNOON MAKES ME WANT TO SPIT!
>> I WANT YOU TO LET IT OUT,
DAWN, BECAUSE THE MINUTE
EVERYTHING COMES OUT YOU'RE
GOING TO BE TEN TIMES STRONGER.
I KNOW THIS.
>> I JUST WANT TO EAT!
I'M SO MAD!
I DON'T EVEN HAVE A COCONUT!
I MEAN, COME ON!
>> JUST KEEP -- DON'T -- JUST
DON'T LOSE HOPE.
DAWN, THIS IS DAY 35!
>> OKAY.
>> FOUR DAYS FROM NOW WE'RE
GOING TO BE -- HAVE BIG SMILES
ON OUR FACES.
I GUARANTEE YOU THAT.
>> I'LL BE BACK IN A FEW
MINUTES.
>> I'M PLAYING THAT THIS WAS A
WONDERFUL THING.
I'M PLAYING THAT THIS WAS THE
RIGHT CHOICE REGARDLESS OF WHAT
MY STOMACH IS SAYING BUT DAWN
DOESN'T FEEL THE SAME.
DAWN IS DEVASTATED, DAWN IS
UPSET.
DAWN IS CRYING.
DAWN IS PISSED OFF.
DAWN IS LIVID.
>> THE THERE WILL BE SOMETHING
WE'LL CRACK UP ABOUT OVER
COOKIES, SPAGHETTI IN THEIR
MOUTH.
PANCAKES, WHATEVER.
WE'RE GOING TO BE CRACKING UP
ABOUT IT.
WHENEVER YOU DO ANYTHING BIG IN
THIS GAME, WHETHER YOU DO
SOMETHING BAD TO SOMEONE, IT'S
FUNNY HOW IT'S ALWAYS A
DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD.
IT CAN BE AMAZING BECAUSE
THEY'RE LIKE "OKAY, I'LL NEVER
VOTE OUT BRENDA BECAUSE I OWE
HER" OR IT COULD BE, BOOM,
DOWNFALL.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YES, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> AT THE TIME BRENDA MADE HER
DECISION TO GIVE UP HER REWARD
AND LET THE FOUR OTHER SURVIVORS
ENJOY IT, IT'S LIKE, OH, MY GOD,
GREEN IS FANTASTIC, SHE IS SHE
FEELLESS, THIS IS A GAME WINNING
-- THAT'S WHEY WHAT MY MOM
WHISPERED.
SHE SAID "BRENDA IS GOING TO WIN
THIS GAME."
>> THANKS FOR EVERYTHING TODAY,
BRENDA.
I LOVE YOU.
>> BUT THE BETTER AND MORE
LIKABLE AND AND MORE UNTOUCHABLE
SEEMS THE MORE PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO WANT TO GET HER OUT BECAUSE
WE'RE AT THAT POINT IN THE GAME
WHERE LIKABILITY IS A LIABILITY
AND I KNOW THAT BETTER THAN
ANYONE ELSE AND I THINK BRENDA
WILL BE EXPERIENCING THAT SOON
IF I HAVE ANY SAY IN IT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ERIK GIVE IT UP.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS
UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE STANDING ON A LEDGE
OVER WATER WHILE HOLDING ON TO A
HANDLE BEHIND YOUR BACK.
THAT HAND IS CONNECTED TO A
WINCH.
EVERY TIME I CRANK IT, IT WILL
LOWER YOU CLOSER TO THE WATER.
WHEN THE PAIN BECOMES TOO MUCH
TO BEAR, YOU'LL FALL INTO THE
WATER AND YOU'RE OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A 1-5 SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE,
AFTER 36 DIFFICULT DAYS,
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR
SPOT.
WE'RE GOING TO BE STANDING
BETWEEN YOUR COLORS WITH YOUR
ARMS BEHIND YOUR BACK.
EVERYBODY NIECE PLACE.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON AND WE'RE
GOING TO GET STARTED RIGHT AWAY
BY LOWERING YOU.
HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK, IT'S
GOING TO BE TOUGH AND YOU'VE GOT
TO BE TENACIOUS TO GET IT DONE.
I KNOW THAT I'VE CLEARLY BEEN ON
THE OUTS FROM THE BEGINNING.
IT'S DEFINITELY MY TURN TO GO
HOME TONIGHT IF I DON'T WIN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'LL JUST
GET YOU WARMED UP.
>> THIS ALREADY SUCKS.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
THIS CHALLENGE IS DESIGNED TO
TEST YOUR WILL.
THIS IS IT.
IF YOU FALL INTO THAT WATER, YOU
WANT TO DO IT BECAUSE YOU COULD
NOT HOLD ON ANY LONGER.
WE'RE GOING LOWER YOU A LITTLE
MORE.
EVERYBODY FEELING IT NOW.
COCHRAN STARTING TO SLIP.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO BE JUMPING
OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
I WANT TO WIN IT BUT IF EDDIE
WINS IMMUNITY IT'S GOING TO BE A
PRETTY STRESSFUL DAY AT CAMP.
>> YOU GO FIRST, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: EDDY IS THIS A BATTLE
BETWEEN WHO'S GOING TO GO IN
FIRST, YOU AND COCHRAN?
>> NO, I'M PRETTY MUCH AT THE
POINT WHERE IF I DON'T WIN I GO
HOME.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN CANNOT HANG ON
ANY LONGER.
COCHRAN FIRST PERSON OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO FIVE.
TIME TO LOWER YOU AGAIN.
EDDIE NOW REALLY STRUGGLING.
TRYING TO HANG IN THERE.
AFTER 36 DAYS, EDDIE DROPS OUT
OF A CHALLENGE THAT MIGHT DO HIM
IN.
ERIK DROPS OUT, ONLY THE WOMEN
REMAIN.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE: DAWN,
SHERRI, AND BRENDA.
PART OF THIS CHALLENGE AT THIS
POINT IS NOT LETTING ANYONE ELSE
KNOW HOW YOU'RE REALLY FEELING.
SHERRI STRUGGLING TO DO THAT.
>> CAN'T DO IT.
AND SHERRI IS NOW OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SIT HERE ALL
DAY, DO YOU?
>> I HAVEN'T HAD ONE.
I'LL SHARE.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THE ARGUMENT,
SDMAUN
>> I'M JUST SAYING I DON'T WANT
TO GO FOR FOUR HOURS AND I
HAVEN'T WON IMMUNITY AND EDDIE'S
OUT.
>> Jeff: WAIT, YOU GUYS ARE
GOING TO STRIKE A DEAL.
>> NO.
>> NO, I'M SAYING LIKE THREE
FOUR HOUR THING.
>> Jeff: SO, DAWN, THE CASE YOU
JUST TRIED TO MAKE IT EDDIE'S
OUT, LET'S JUST VOTE HIM OUT,
YOU'RE SAFE, YOU'VE WON IMMUNITY
LET ME HAVE THE EXPERIENCE.
>> YES.
BUT THAT'S OKAY.
I KNOW BRENDA WANTS TO CHALLENGE
HERSELF AND I RESPECT IT.
>> Jeff: DOWN TO TWO.
THE DAWN ON ONE END, BRENDA ON
THE OTHER.
GOING TO LOWER YOU A LITTLE
CLOSER TO THE WATER.
HERE WE GO.
BOTH WOMEN WAY OUT THERE.
BOTH WOMEN FIGHTING THAT GRIP,
TRYING TO HOLD ON, KEEP THAT
BLOOD PUMPING THROUGH THERE.
THIS IS IT.
THE TWO WOMEN WHO DID NOT SPEND
TIME WITH THEIR LOVED ONES
BATTLING IT OUT.
>> YES!
JUST LIKE THAT BRENDA CANNOT
HANG ON.
DAWN WINS IMMUNITY AND IS
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FIVE!
>> THAT WAS CLOSE.
>> ALL RIGHT, DAWN, COME ON
OVER.
(APPLAUSE)
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN HER
"SURVIVOR" CAREER, DAWN IS
WEARING THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
DAWN IS SAFE AFTER 36 DAYS IN
THIS GAME.
YOU WILL LIVE TO SAY DAY 37.
YOU HAVE A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FIVE.
UNFORTUNATELY EDDIE, COCHRAN,
BRENDA, ERIK, SHERRI, ONE OF YOU
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL,
CONGRATS.
>> THANK YOU!
YAY!
>> I NEVER, EVER WANT TO BE THAT
PERSON THAT JUMPS INTO THE WATER
THAT GIVES UP IMMUNITY.
IF THAT WAS EDDIE UP THERE I
WOULD HAVE HUNG ON A LOT LONGER.
BUT SOMEONE AS PARANOID AS DAWN,
GOT TO KEEP HER HAPPY, JUMPED IN
THE WATER.
IT WAS ALL GOOD.
THAT FELT GOOD.
>> THE WHOLE CHALLENGE TODAY WAS
TO MAKE SURE EDDIE DIDN'T WIN
IMMUNITY AND AS SOON AS EDDIE
JUMPED IN THE WATER IT WAS LIKE
GLEE ALL OVER MY FACE.
I HAVE TO WORK ON THAT BECAUSE I
FELT BAD SHOWING HOW HAPPY I WAS
>> MY ARMS FEEL LIKE SPAGHETTI.
>> I THINK IT'S A
STRAIGHTFORWARD VOTE TONIGHT.
EDDIE'S GOING HOME AND AFTER
EDDIE THE PLAN IS TO TAKE OUT
COCHRAN.
IN MY HEAD IT'S THE PERFECT PLAN
IF WE CAN JUST STICK TO IT
EVERYTHING WILL GO AMAZING.
THIS IS EXTREMELY
STRAIGHTFORWARD.
I KNOW IT.
>> YUP.
>> RIGHT?
>> IF I HAD MY PICK BETWEEN
EDDIE AND BRENDA, PERSONALLY I'D
LIKE TO HAVE BRENDA GO.
I THINK IT'S A GREAT MOVE THAT
BENEFITS ME AND EVEN INDIRECTLY
BENEFITS DAWN AND SHERRI.
BUT I'M THINKING, OKAY, THE
PROBLEM WITH THAT IS THAT
EVERYBODY IS SO GUNG-HO ABOUT
GETTING EDDIE OUT.
IT'S A FOREGONE CONCLUSION WHEN
WE GOT BACK TO CAMP SO I THOUGHT
THIS IS GOING TO BE A PRETTY
HARD SELL.
SOME THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'VE
GUARANTEED OURSELVES FINAL FOUR.
LIKE, YOU REALIZE THAT, RIGHT?
>> YES.
ABSOLUTELY.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT TONIGHT.
I'M RUNNING THROUGH IT.
>> CAN I GUESS WHAT YOUR
SCENARIO IS GOING TO BE?
>> SURE.
>> BLIND SIDE BRENDA TONIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> BECAUSE SHE'D NEVER SEE IT
COMING.
I WAS ALREADY THERE.
>> IT IS THE PERFECT MOVE
BECAUSE TONIGHT IS THE PERFECT
NIGHT TO MAKE IT.
IF BRENDA HAD ONE MORE DAY IN
THIS GAME SHE COULD UPSET
EVERYTHING.
THERE ARE ONLY A FEW DAYS LEFT.
SHE COULD GO ON A WINNING STREAK
WIN AT THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I'M MAKING SURE THAT DOESN'T
HAPPEN.
BRENDA IS A BIG THREAT.
>> AGREED AND WE KNOW SHE'S --
>> SHE HASN'T BETRAYED A SINGLE
PERSON, SHE ALLOWED PEOPLE TO
SEE THEIR LOVED ONES, SHE WON
IMMUNITY.
>> SO LET'S SAY THAT LEAVES
EDDIE AND EDDIE WINS THE LAST
CHALLENGE AND THEN WE'RE LEFT AT
KIND OF THE MERCY OF EDDIE'S
DECISION MAKING ON WHO GOES TO
THE END.
>> YOU THINK EDDIE STAYING IN
THE GAME IS A BIG THREAT?
>> THERE IS A PART OF ME THAT MY
GUT TELLS ME BRENDA'S KIND OF
STAY THE COURSE.
EVERYTHING'S FALLEN INTO PLACE
SO I'M GUESSING IN HER MIND
SHE'S THINKING EDDIE CAME DOWN
TODAY, NEXT WILL BE EITHER
SHERRI OR COCHRAN.
SHE'S NOT MARRIED TO IT.
I MEAN, WE KNEW IT WAS GOING TO
GET HARD YOU KNOW?
I'M STILL LOCKED TO YOU BUT I
DIDN'T PLAY MY OWN GAME LAST
TIME SO I'M TRYING TO AND IT'S
JUST HARD.
THIS IS A POINT WHERE THERE'S A
FORK.
THE WORST-CASE SCENARIO IS WE
TAKE EDDIE OUT TONIGHT LIKE WE
SAY AND WE DEAL WITH THIS EXACT
SAME THING TOMORROW, RIGHT?
>> OKAY, WE CAN STICK WITH EDDIE
THEN.
>> THERE IS THE KIND OF THE PART
WHERE IT'S SO EASY TO GET RID OF
BRENDA IT'S TANTALIZING.
>> AGREED.
ORIGINALLY I THOUGHT VOTE OUT
EDDIE BUT BRENDA IS THE BIGGEST
STRATEGIC THREAT IN THIS GAME TO
WIN IT AND MY APPROACH ALL ALONG
HAD BEEN TO TAKE OUT THE BIGGEST
STRATEGIC THREAT AND I KNOW SHE
DOESN'T HAVE IMMUNITY AND I KNOW
SHE'S NOT EXPECTING IT AND I
KNOW IT WILL ONLY TAKE THREE
VOTES TO GET HER TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
>> WHAT I FEEL LIKE IS MAYBE I'M
A LITTLE BIT SWAYED BY COCHRAN'S
EMOTION AND LAST TIME I LEFT MY
GAME A LITTLE BIT IN HIS HANDS
AND HE CONTROLLED IT AND I WENT
HOME BEFORE HIM AND I DON'T WANT
TO DO THAT THIS TIME.
I'M REALLY CONFUSED.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
MIKE, PHILLIP, MALCOLM, REYNOLD
AND ANDREA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, DAWN, WEARING THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE FOR THE FIRST TIME
AFTER ALL THE DAYS YOU'VE PLAYED
THIS THIS GAME, HOW DOES IT
FEEL?
>> YEAH, IT FEELS GOOD COME TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND JUST BREATHE
AND JUST NOT WORRY SO MUCH.
I'M GLAD TO BE SAFE BUT MORE
THAN ANYTHING IT WAS A FEELING
OF I DID THAT, I TRAINED FOR
THIS GAME AND I CAME AND DID
SOMETHING IT'S LIKE A BUCKETLESS
THING.
>> BRENDA, WHAT'S THE FEELING
WHERE YOU KNOW I'M AT MY END AND
THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON LEFT?
>> IN THIS CASE IT WAS OKAY
BECAUSE IT WAS DAWN.
I WANTED HER TO WIN IT VERSUS ME
JUST JUMPING OFF AND I THOUGHT
I'VE GOT FIVE MORE MINUTES MAX
ON THIS THING AND THEN I FELL
OFF.
>> Jeff: SO EDDIE, ON THE OTHER
SIDE YOU FELT THE PRESSURE-- AS
YOU HAVE GOING BACK TO DAY ONE--
BUT YOU NEEDED TO WIN.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IF I DIDN'T WIN I WAS PROBABLY
PACKING MY BAGS FOR THE LAST
TIME AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: AND YET HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE YOU SAID THAT AT TRIBAL?
>> YEAH, I KNOW, KIND OF LIKE A
BROKEN RECORD.
BUT MY AMIGO FUSE IS RUNNING A
LITTLE BIT SHORT.
>> Jeff: SO THERE WAS ANOTHER
BIG EVENT.
FINALLY THE LOVED ONES.
BRENDA GETS TO THE LOVED ONE
CHALLENGE AND YOU WIN AND YOU'RE
FACED WITH A BIG DILEMMA.
>> TO JUST THINK WOW, MY GOD,
I'M STANDING NEXT TO MY DAD AND
THEN MY SISTER IS HERE AND THEN
THE DILEMMA COMES.
IT WAS EITHER TWO OF US OR FOUR
OF THEM AND IT WAS A NO-BRAINER.
IT WAS HARD AND EASY AT THE SAME
TIME.
>> DAWN, DOES A GESTURE FROM
BRENDA BUY HER ANYTHING IN THIS
GAME?
>> I THINK IT DOES BUY HER
SOMETHING.
EVERYTHING WAS REALLY HAPPY.
I WOULD THEY THE LONG-TERM ON
THAT IS GOING TO BENEFIT HER IN
THE GAME.
>> Jeff: SHERRI WOULD YOU AGREE
WITH THAT?
>> DEFINITE LIFT SERVE LOOKING
TO BRENDA AS A SAINT AND YOU
COULDN'T DO ANYTHING TO HER
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff:, COCHRAN, ON ONE HAND
THERE'S AN EASY VOTE TONIGHT.
IT'S EDDIE.
BUT NOTHING ABOUT THIS SEASON
HAD BEEN EASY OR PREDICTABLE.
>> YEAH, EDDIE IS AN EASY VOTE
BUT THE EASY VOTE ISN'T ALWAYS
THE SMARTEST VOTE.
IT'S ABOUT WEIGHING SHORT-TERM
GRATIFICATION VERSUS LONG-TERM
BENEFITS AND THAT'S A CONSTANT
STRUGGLE IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: SO, EDDIE, WHAT ARE THE
ODDS TONIGHT THAT YOU SURVIVE?
>> I REALLY THINK THIS IS THE
FINAL SENDOFF FOR MYSELF BUT
I'VE SO COME TO TERMS WITH IT
ALREADY.
ONE THING AFTER ANOTHER HAS BEEN
EVEN MORE UNBELIEVABLE THAN THE
LAST AND I'M GOING TO BE FOREVER
GRATEFUL TO EVERYBODY HERE.
I'VE HAD THE BEST TIME.
I REALLY HAVE.
I'VE HAD THE BEST TIME HERE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
DAWN IS NOT GOING HOME.
EDDIE IS PRETTY SURE HE IS GOING
HOME.
(LAUGHTER)
LET'S FIND OUT WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
COCHRAN, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, EDDIE.
EDDIE.
TWO VOTES EDDIE.
ERIK.
TWO VOTES EDDIE; ONE VOTE ERIK.
BRENDA.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES BRENDA; TWO VOTES
EDDIE, ONE VOTE ERIK, ONE VOIGT
LEFT.
15th PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
SIXTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
BRENDA.
>> I KNEW IT.
>> YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
>> I WAS LON WEST YOU GUYS, I
WAS GENUINE WITH YOU GUYS.
>> BRENDA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> IT HURTS.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE MADE IT TO
THE FINAL FIVE.
YOU HAVE THREE DAYS LEFT IN THIS
GAME AND IF THE FIRST 36 ARE ANY
INDICATION IT'S GOING TO BE A
CRAZY FINISH.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON "SURVIVOR"
-- WITH ONLY THREE DAYS LEFT --
IN WHAT HAS BEEN A COMPLETELY
UNPREDICTABLE SEASON THE FINAL
FIVE PUT IT ALL ON THE LINE.
>> IT'S MY GAME TO LOSE.
>> Jeff: UNTIL ONE SURVIVOR GOES
DOWN.
>> THIS GAME JUST GOT ROCKED
AGAIN.
TUNE IN SUNDAY, MAY 12.
(SOBBING)
I'M JUST CRYING BECAUSE IT WAS
-- I'M IN SHOCK.
I THINK THE REASON IT HURTS SO
MUCH IS THAT I WAS HESITANT TO
LIE TO PEOPLE.
I WAS SO TRUE TO DAWN.
OH, MY GOD, IT JUST HURTS SO
MUCH RIGHT NOW.