>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"."
>> YOUR BEHAVIOR IS NOT
ACCEPTABLE.
>> SHUT UP!
>> Jeff: WHILE THE FANS CAMP
WAS FILLED WITH DISORDER, THE
ONLY THING COMING TOGETHER WAS
THE COUPLE'S ALLIANCE.
>> WE HAVE THIS FOUR WITH ME,
EDDIE, ALLIE AND HOPE.
>> Jeff: THE FAVORITES HAD A
CLEAR DIVISION-- PHILLIP'S
ALLIANCE, STEALTHRUS," WAS
CALLING THE SHOTS.
>> HE'S TREATING PEOPLE LIKE
GARBAGE AND I DON'T LIKE THAT.
YOU GOTTA CUT THE HEAD OFF THE
SNAKE.
FRIGGIN' INSPECTOR IMAGEET
THOUGHT HE COULD PULL HIS
SPECIAL AGENT TRIMCH TRICKS BUT
YOU DON'T WANT TO FIGHT WITH ME.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, FAVORITES WON EASILY.
FAVORITES WIN IMMUNITY AND
REWARD!
WITH THE FANS FACING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, REYNOLD WAS VOCAL ABOUT
WANTING SHAMAR OFF THE ISLAND.
>> I'M GOING TO VOTE FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN, SO THAT'S
GOOD, VOTE.
>> Jeff: BUT JERRI HAD OTHER
PLANS.
>> YOU WANT YOU ON OUR SIDE.
I WANT SHAMAR TO KEEP ANNOYING
PEEMPLE BECAUSE SHAMAR IS MY
PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: SHE RECRUITED SHAMAR
AND TRIED TO PERSUADE THE TRIBE
TO BREAK UP THE COUPLES
ALLIANCE.
>> I JUST NEED TO MAKE A
DECISION AND IT'S NOT GOING TO
BE EASY ONE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
REYNOLD REVEALED HIS IDOL.
>> JEFF, I'M HOLDING THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL THEY FOUND ON
ISLAND.
>> Jeff: BUT IT DIDN'T SWAY
THE TRIBE FROM VOTING OUT HIS
CLOSEST ALLY.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF "FANS
VS. FAVORITES," ALLIE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: 18 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> THAT WAS CRAZY, I KNOW THAT.
>> I WAS SWEATING IT COMING BACK
TO CAMP BECAUSE I WAS THE ONE
THAT WAS AT THE CROSSROADS OF
THE TWO ALIENLSES.
AND IT TOOK MAYBE LESS THAN 30
SECONDS FOR THOINGZ HIT THE FAN.
>> WE ARE NOT FRIEND.
BUT WE NEED EACH OTHER TO WIN.
>> WE DO.
>> YOU NEED ME TO WINL
CHALLENGES.
>> YUP.
>> I HAVE AN IDOL AND I'LL
( BLEEP ) PLAY IT.
I WAS GOOD TO HOLD IT AND USE IT
FOR THE GOOD OF THE TRIBE.
I DON'T TRUST ANYONE HERE NOW.
SO GAME ON.
>> I WANTED TO SAY HOW THE GAME
JUST STARTED BECAUSE I DIDN'T
GET VOTED OUT BECAUSE YOUR PLAN
DIDN'T WORK, NOW IT'S GAME ON.
>> SHAMAR, IT WASN'T OUR PLAN,
DUDE.
>> IT WAS YOUR PLAN.
YOU ALL WROTE MY NAME DOWN.
SO IT WAS YOUR PLAN.
>> DON'T SAY, OH, NOW IT'S A
GAME."
I THOUGHT WE WERE ONE HAPPY
FAMILY BECAUSE I DIDN'T GET
VOTED OUT.
NOW IT'S LIKE WE CAN'T BE A
FAMILY NOW, RIGHT.
>> IT WASN'T MY PLAN.
YOU KNOW WHO ASKED ME?
>> I DON'T WANT KNOW.
>> IT WASN'T ONE OF MY
ALLIANCE.
>> HE SAID, I'M VOTING FOR
SHAMAR.
AND AND HE THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
GOING TO VOTE FOR HIM.
>> TRIBE RIGHT NOW IS SO
DRAMATIC.
I HATE IT.
>> THE CAMP IS TOTALLY IN CHAOS.
YOU WOULD THINK BECAUSE I SAVED
SHAMAR'S AS, HE WOULD SHUT UP.
>> I DID NOT COME AT-- DID I SAY
IT TO YOU?
DID I SAY IT TO YOU?
>> I'M NOT HERE TO ARGUE WITH
YOU, SHAMAR.
>> YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT ARGUING
BECAUSE YOU'RE ( BLEEP ) RIGHT
NOW.
>> SHAMAR GOT MORE AND MORE
AMPED UP, ALL THE STUFF THAT
HAPPENED AT TRIBAL AND THE DAYS
BEFORE AND HE WAS YELL AT
EVERYBODY.
>> YOU'RE SAYING SORRY NOW.
THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT IS.
THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT
YOURSELF, AND I'M STRONG AND YOU
KNOW IT.
>> KNOW THAT HE HAS BEEN THROUGH
A HELL OF A LOT MORE THAN THE
REST OF US HAVE BEEN.
YOU KNOW, HE'S HAD TWO TIEWRTZ
IN IRAQ.
>> I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO SAID
THAT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING TO
ME!
IF I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE!
YOU JUST SAID I WASN'T THE ONLY
ONE WHO SAID IT.
WHY ARE YOU GETTING ON ME THEN?
>> AT THE SAME TIME, THE PART OF
SHAMAR THAT WAS FUN HAS
COMPLETELY GONE.
>> YOU WERE WRONG!
I WASN'T TALKED TO YOU!
WE'RE IN A TIGHT SPOT NOW,
FRIENDO.
>> WE GOT OUR HEADS CHOPPED OFF.
>> I KNOW.
REVENGE OF THE NERDS.
WE WEE JUST HAD TRIBAL COUNCIL
LAST NIGHT AND WE PRETTY MUCH
GOT BLIND SIDED.
I THOUGHT WE WERE ALL ON THE
SAME PAGE ABOUT VOTING SHAMAR
OFF FOR NOT CONTRIBUTING TO
CAMP.
CONGRATULATIONS TO THEM, THEY
GOT US.
>> I'M ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK
BEFORE YOU.
>> HOW ARE YOU BEFORE ME?
>> IT'S PROBABLY A MASS MINORITY
NOW.
>> UNTIL SHAMAR PISSES OFF
SOMEBODY ELSE TODAY.
>> SHAMAR, YOU WANT A COCONUT?
>> NO.
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT SHAMAR
IS FREELOADING AND BEING LAZY.
AND I THINK SHAMAR IS GOING TO
STEP ON TOO MANY PEOPLE'S TOES
ON HIS OWN AND THEY'RE GOING TO
BE LIKE NOW IS THE TIME FOR HIM
TO GO.
I WANT HIM GONE.
>> TODAY, DO YOUR BEST, ABSOLUTE
BEST, EVEN IF THEY GET ON YOUR
NERVES,EVEN IF YOU WANT TO WRING
THEIR NECKS, JUST KEEP YOUR
MOUTH SHOT.
>> THEY KNOW THEY'RE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
THE NEXT EASY TARGET IS GOING TO
BE YOU BECAUSE YOU'RE VOCAL.
>> I WAS THE EASY TARGET BEFORE.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE VOCAL.
>> I'M ALWAYS GOING TO BE THE
EASY TARGET.
>> EXACTLY.
>> I'M NOT A QUITTER BUT THESE
ARE CHILDISH, IMMATURE GAMES--
>> THAT'S PART OF THIS WHOLE
CRAZY GAME.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> IT MAY NOT BE YOUR GAME BUT
THAT'S PART OF THE GAME.
YOU DON'T RUN ACROSS SHAMARS
EVERY DAY BUT IN MY LIFE I HAVE
COME ACROSS PEOPLE WITH THAT
KIND OF ATTITUDE.
I OWN SEVERAL FRANCHISES WHO
EVERYBODY WHO WORKS FOR ME IS
UNDER THE AGE OF, SAY, 24, SO
THAT'S ALL I DO IS DEAL WITH
SNOTTY, TEENAGED BRATS ALL DAY
SO I THINK I'M THE CLOSEST ONE
WHO UNDERSTANDS HOW HE THINKS
OUT HERE BUT HE NEEDS TO SHUT
UP.
>> I UNDERSTAND IT WAS A GAME
BUT I'M GOING TO KEEP SITTING
HERE AND LYING.
>> BUT THEY WILL.
>> BUT I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> I'M OVER IT.
I DON'T REALLY CARE.
I CAN'T DO ( BLEEP ).
THIS AIN'T MY KIND OF LIFESTYLE,
MAN.
I'M JUST KIND OF FEEL LIKE IN
THIS GAME, I'M LIKE THE BLACK
SHEEP.
I HONESTLY CAME INTO THIS GAME
REALLY WANTING THE MILLION
DOLLARS BUT WHEN I ACTUALLY SEEN
HOW PEOPLE ACT, IT'S KIND OF
LIKE-- IT'S NOT REALLY WORTH IT
TO ME.
THAT'S WHERE IT'S KIND OF
DISHEARTENING.
THAT'S WHERE I QUESTION, YOU
KNOW, HOW MUCH I SHOULD BE IN
THIS GAME
>> I'M 54 YEARS OLD.
TO BE PLAYING "SURVIVOR" AGAIN,
I'M ACTUALLY HAVING THE TIME OF
MY LIFE RIGHT NOW.
54 IS JUST A NUMBER.
AND TO BE HONEST WITH YOU, IN MY
DAILY LIFE, I REALLY KNOW HOW TO
TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
I REALLY KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
I WORK OUT.
FOR MY AGE, TO DO WHAT I DO,
IT'S PHENOMENAL.
WHEN I GO TO THE GYM NOW AND I
PLAY FOUR-COURT BALL, I'M
PLAYING WITH MEN HALF MY AGE.
AND I HAVE A LITTLE THING.
I GET A LITTLE REBOUND, SPRINT
TO THE CORNER WITH IT.
DOUBLE DRIBBLE.
GO FOR IT, ONE STEP BACK, ALL
AIR, BABY.
PLAYING WITH GUYS TWICE MY
HEIGHT.
LIKE THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO OUT THERE.
AND THEY CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M
DOING.
"HEY, MAN, YOU'RE PLAYING PRO
NBA BALL."
NOT, YOU'RE JUST NOT USED TO THE
LARRY BIRD.
I'M OLD SCHOOL.
>> WHAT WILL WE DO WHEN THERE'S
A SWITCH AND SOME PEOPLE ARE
LEFT HERE DO WE GIVE THEM BEANS.
>> ANDREA AND PHILLIP HAVE
PLAYED TOGETHER AND HAVE A
CONNECTION, AND COCHRAN AND DAWN
HAVE PLAYED TOGETHER AND HAVE A
CONNECTION SO THAT REALLY LEFT
MALCOLM AND I AND WE GRAVITATED
TOWARDS EACH OTHER.
>> THERE ARE A MILLION PLACES IT
COULD BE.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
>> IT HAS TO BE NEAR SOMETHING.
IT HAS TO BE CATFISH.
HE'S SUPER SMART.
HE WENT TO AN IVY LEAGUE SCHOOL.
AND IT DOESN'T HURT TO HAVE
SOMEBODY GOOD LOOKING AROUND.
>> THAT'S GROSS.
>> REACH AROUND-- NO WAY.
>> NO!
>> DO YOU THINK IT'S A CLUE OR
DO YOU THINK IT'S AN IDOL?
I'M SO EXCITED.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, YOU FOUND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
FINALLY I GOT SOME POWER IN
MYBACK POCKET.
♪ I GOT THE IDOL NAH-NAH-NAH ♪ ♪
>> WE'LL BURY IT.
>> I'M NOT THRILLED CORINNE
KNOWS I HAVE THE IDOL.
OF COURSE IN A PERFECT WORLD I
WOULD HAVE IT ALL TO MYSELF BUT
CORINNE DOES KNOW ABOUT IT AND
SHE'S SOMEONE WHO LUCKILY I DID
HAVE A GOOD RELATIONSHIP WITH
EARLY ON THIS GAME.
OUR WAGONS KIND OF HITCHED
TOGETHER BECAUSE OF THIS IDOL
NOW.
IT'S GOING TO WORK OUT VERY WELL
OR WE'RE GOING TO BURN DOWN
QUICKLY BECAUSE SHE WILL NOT GO
DOWN WITHOUT A FIGHT.
>> NOBODY JOONS NOBODY KNOWS.
>> DONE.
GAME, SET, MATCH.
>> WHAT IT DOES IS, WHEN THE
WIND BLOWS, IT TRAPS THE AIR AND
MAKES LIKE A CIRCULAR AND IT
COOLS YOU.
>> BACK AT HOME, I'M WAITING THE
WHOLE WEEK LONG FOR WEDNESDAY
NIGHT TO ARRIVE SO I CAN TURN ON
CBS AND SEE WHAT'S IN STORE.
CAN I SIT IN THE MAGICAL SEAT,
PHIL?
>> YES, YOU CAN SIT IN THE SEAT.
I CROWN YOU.
>> BUT WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING THIS
GAME EVERY SINGLE DAY IS LIKE
WEDNESDAY NIGHT AT EIGHT.
IT'S WILD.
I GET TO WATCH "SURVIVOR" WHILE
I'M PLAYING "OF "SURVIVOR."
AND FOR A "SURVIVOR" NUT LIKE
ME, IT'S GREAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE IN THIS
WORLD DON'T DO THIS.
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT A
SPECIALIST.
>> IT'S NOT NORMAL FOR ME TO BE
SURROUNDED BY THESE BEAUTIFUL
WOMEN WHO ARE HALF THE TIME JUST
WEARING THEIR UNDERWEAR.
THAT'S SOME SORT OF FREUDIAN
PICNIC, I THINK, BUT IT'S REAL
HERE.
>> IT'S A GOOD THING THAT
THERE'S AN IDOL BETWEEN US
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY
PEOPLE REALLY WANT YOU TO GO TO
THE VERY END.
>> WHY ARE THEY, LIKE, INTENSELY
TALKING?
>> I JUST DON'T GET WHAT THEIR
LOYALTIES ARE.
>> I'VE LEARNED FROM THE LAST
TIME I PLAYED THAT YOU HAVE TO
ALWAYS BE THINKING.
EVEN IF YOU THINK YOU HAVE A
GROUP, IT'S SOLILD, THERE COULD
BE BETTER OPTIONS AND I REALLY
WANT CORINNE OUT.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE MALCOLM IS
AT, BUT DOESN'T CORINNE WORRY
YOU?
>> YES.
>> WE HAVE A SIX AND LET'S JUST
HANG OUT AND SHE'S HAVING SO
MANY ONE-ON-ONE INTENSE
CONVERSATIONS WITH EVERYBODY.
>> HER AND MALCOLM ARE
REMARKABLY CLOSE.
>> YOU SAW THEM TALKING.
WHAT IF WE COULD GET A UNANIMOUS
VOTE.
US FIVE ARE CLOSE.
YOU'RE CLOSE TO BRANDON, RIGHT.
>> YES.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE'D MAKE A
MOVE RIGHT NOW BUT I WANT TO GET
HER OUT OF HERE BEFORE SHEIK GET
RID OF ME.
I THINK CORINNE AND MALCOLM ARE
REALLY CLOSE.
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT THE--
>> I DEFINITELY WANT WANT TO DO
THAT.
>> I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE ON THE
SAME PAGE AS ME.
IT'S HARD BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO TALK TO THE WRONG PERSON TOO
EARLY AND IT GETS BACK TO
CORINNE THAT I'M THINKING ABOUT
SOMETHING, AND THEN ITS TARGET'S
ON ME.
>> WE DON'T WANT YOU TO BE NEXT
TO GO, AND IF YOU STAY WITH US,
IT COULD BE SOMETHING.
>> I FEEL LIKE THIS IS A CHANCE
TO ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW, BE A PART
OF SOMETHING ACTUAL LEGIT NOW.
>> WOULD YOU DO ANYTHING?
>> ANYTHING.
I'M NOT PLAYING THE SAME GAME I
USED TO.
>> CORINNE.
>> ANY QUESTIONS?
>> NO.
I'M GOOD.
I'VE BEEN TOLD THAT I'M SAFE.
"YOU'RE SAFE, YOU'RE SAFE,
YOU'RE SAFE."
BUT IT'S REALLY SKETCHY BECAUSE
THERE'S A VOICE IN THE BACK OF
MY HEAD THAT SAYS, "YOU'VE BEEN
DONE LIKE THIS BEFORE.
YOU'VE BEEN COAXED ALONG TO
BELIEVE SOMETHING THAT IS NOT
TRUE."
>> DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
IT'S HUSH-HUSH.
>> I THINK THERE'S A LOT OF
LYING GOING ON.
THEY TELL ME, "HEY, BRANDON,
YOU'RE GOING OUT NEXT."
I'LL PEE IN THE RICE.
I'LL PEE IN THE BEANS.
I'LL BURN THE SHELTER TO THE
GROUND.
I THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
>> GOOD TALK, THOUGH.
>> GOOD TALK.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
REALLY APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
I'M GOING TO TRY 150% EACH AND
EVERY CHALLENGE, BUT IF WE LOSE
AND MY EFFORTS AREN'T GOOD
ENOUGH FOR THEM TO KEEP MEAN
AROUND, BY GOD, I'M GOING TO
BE-- THERE'S GOING TO BE HELL TO
PAY IN CAMP.
>> MY HAPPINESS IS NOT WORTH A
MILLION.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE THE ANGRY
BLACK MAN ON "SURVIVOR."
IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
IT'S JUST NOT.
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF HAPPY
THOUGHTS HERE.
AND IT REALLY SUCKS IF I HAVE TO
QUIT THIS GAME, BUT IT'S, LIKE,
IS NOT QUITTING NOT WORTH NOT
BEING HAPPY?
AND THAT'S WHERE, YOU KNOW, IT'S
A NO-BRAINER TO ME.
>> I MEAN, I KNOW YOUR DECISION
IS PROBABLY MADE UP AT THIS
POINT.
( LAUGHS."
>> BUT I JUST WANT YOU KNOW THAT
I'D LOVE FOR YOU TO STAY.
>> STOP IT, LAURA!
>> REALLY, SHAMAR.
I THINK BECAUSE WE'RE ALL SUCH
BIG FANS OF THE SHOW WE WERE ALL
A LITTLE BIT THROWN BACK BY THE
FACT THAT SHAMAR WOULD TAKE IT
SO FAR AS TO QUIT.
>> AFTER I CAME HOME FROM IRAQ,
I HAD A VERY TOUGH TIME
ADJUSTING TO LIFE OUTSIDE OF THE
MILITARY.
I WAS AN ALCOHOLIC.
AND I HAD A LOT OF ANGER ISSUES.
WHEN I FIRST CAME HOME, PEOPLE
WERE LIKE EVEN SCARED TO BE
AROUND ME.
BECAUSE I WAS IN THAT DARK
PLACE, LIKE PEOPLE DIDN'T KNOW
HOW I WAS GOING TO REACT TO
THINGS.
THEY DIDN'T KNOW WHAT I WAS
GOING TO DO.
THERE WAS SITUATIONS THAT
HAPPENED IN IRAQ THAT, YOU KNOW,
IT WAS HARD FOR ME TO LIVE WITH
YOU KNOW.
I WATCHED SUICIDE BOMBINGS IN
FRONT OF ME.
I SEEN MY FRIENDS IN BODY BAGS,
AND I'VE JUST BEEN IN A LOT OF
TIGHT SITUATIONS THAT I JUST
CAN'T FORGET ABOUT.
AFTER SOME TIME, I LEARNED TO
LOVE MYSELF, AND I GOT OUT OF
THAT DARK PLACE.
I COME HERE.
I TRY TO BE A HAPPY PERSON.
I TRY TO UPLIFT EVERYBODY.
AND EVERYTHING IS SHAMAR'S DOING
THIS.
SHAMAR'S DOING THAT.
CERTAIN PEOPLE TALKING TO ME
CONDESCENDINGLY AND IT'S JUST
PUTTING ME IN THE ANGER ROOM.
SO THAT'S WHY I'M REALLY
LEAVING.
IT'S JUST-- I WANT TO GET THAT
HAPPINESS BACK IN MY LIFE.
>> I'M JUST SCARED SHAMAR YOU'RE
GOING TO LOOK BACK AND REGRET
IT.
>> REGRET WHAT?
I KNOW THAT IT'S NOT GOING TO
GET REQUEST BETTER.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
OVER IN IRAQ.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY PEOPLE HE
KILLED.
I DON'T KNOW WHY HE'S GOING TO
THIS DARK PLACE BUT I REALLY
BELIEVE HE'S GOING TO LOOK BACK
IF HE QUITS AND-- HE'S NOT
REALIZING WHAT HE'S DOING TO
HIMSELF IF HE QUITS.
I MEAN, THE THING THAT SUCKS IS
IF YOU DECIDE TO LEAVE AND THEN
WE END UP LOSING AND HAVE TO GO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, THAT WE HAVE
TO THEN VOTE OUT SOMEBODY ELSE.
>> THAT'S THE THING IS THAT
WE'LL BE DOWN TWO IF YOU QUIT.
>> YOU'RE MY LADIES.
I FEEL LIKE IN TALKING TO YOU
GUYS, AND ME SAYING, WELL, I
RESPECT LOYALTY AND LOYALTY
MEANS EVERYTHING TO ME.
AND YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN LOYAL TO
ME.
SO I FEEL LIKE I'D BE DOING YOU
A DISSERVICE TO JUST LEAVE YOU
RIGHT NOW.
JUST WHEN I KNOW HOW LOYAL YOU
HAVE BEEN ON, AND YOU GUYS
ACTUALLY STUCK UP FOR ME, SO, I
REALLY RESPECT THAT.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT I'LL STAY
AND FIGHT FOR YOU GUYS A FEW
MORE DAYS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I HAD MY HOPES UP A LITTLE
BIT THAT SHAMAR WOULD QUIT, BUT
DEEP DOWN I KNEW HE WOULDN'T
FOLLOW THROUGH ITW IT AND HE'D
TURN IT INTO THIS, LIKE, SHAMAR
IS ALL ABOUT LOYALTY AND MADE
HIMSELF A HERO FOR UNQUITTING
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR" THAT
50,000 PEOPLE WOULD LINE UP FOR
DAYS JUST TO GET A CHANCE TO
PLAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S NO HER OAK MOVE IN MY
BOOK, BUT I'M JUST GOING TO PLAY
MY GAME, AND SHAMAR IS JUST
GOING TO BE ONE OF THE FACTORS
IN MY GAME AND I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> WHOOO!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES GETTING
YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW TRIBE
OF FANS.
ALLIE VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BRANDON,
WAR CRY OR NOT, TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, BOTH
TRIBES WILL RACE OUT INTO THE
WATER TO A LARGE BAMBOO CAGE.
YOU'LL CLIMB OVER THE CAGE AND
INTO THE WATER WHERE YOU WILL
FIND A VERY HEAVY CHEST.
YOU MUST THEN UNTIE THE CAGE
DOOR AND DRAG THE CHEST THROUGH
THE CAGE AND ALL THE WAY BACK TO
SHORE.
YOU'LL THEN PLACE THE CHEST ON A
TRACK AND USE A GRAPPLING RING
TO RETRIEVE THREE MISSING
SECTIONS OF TRACK.
YOU WILL THEN PUSH YOUR CHEST TO
THE FINISH.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET THEIR CHEST
ON THE FINISH PLATFORM WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YES!
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: COMFORT.
>> YES!
>> CHAIRS!
( APPLAUSE )
>> HELLO!
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE CHAIRS,
PILLOW AND A BLANKET AND YOU
ALSO HAVE A TARP.
>> YES!
>> OH, MAN!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE ARE
EVEN UP, 9-9.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
EVERYBODY IN THE WATER.
SOME STRONG SWIMS, OR BOTH
TRIBES.
AND SOME NOT-SO-STRONG SWIMMERS
ON BOTH TRIBES.
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR WAY UP AND
OVER THIS CAGE BUT YOU CAN'T
START WORKING ON THE KNOTS OR
START DRAGGING THE CHEST UNTIL
EVERYBODY'S OVER
LAURA WAY BACK.
SHE IS ON HER OWN.
>> COME ON, LAURA!
>> OPENING THE DOOR FOR THE
FAVORITES AND A BIG LEAD.
REYNOLD GOING BACK TO GIVE HER A
HAND.
>>> Jeff: A LOT OF
TENTATIVENESS ON BOTH TRIBES
RIGHT NOW.
FAVORITES ARE ALL IN.
START WORKING!
FANS ARE ALL IN.
YOU HAVE TO UNTIE THE FRONT
DISPERSANT OF THE CAGE.
>> SOMEBODY TOOK THE GOGGLES.
I WEAR CONTACTS.
I CAN'T SEE.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> WHERE'S THE GOGGLES?
>> Jeff: FANS ARE THROUGH!
START DRAGGING THAT CHEST!
FAVORITES ARE FALLING BEHIND.
FAVORITES NOW HAVE RELEASED
THEIR CAGE.
BOTH TRIBES ARE NOW DRAGGING
THEIR CHEST
GREAT WORK BY THE FANS.
THEY ARE MOVING EN MASS TOWARD
THAT BEACH.
FAVORITES STILL TRYING TO GET A
SYSTEM GOING
FAVORITES FALLING FURTHER BEHIND
NOW.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: IT IS VERY HEAVY.
IT TAKES ALL NINE TRIBE MEMBERS
TO LIFT THIS CHEST.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, THE
FAVORITES HAVE NOW CAUGHT UP
BOTH TRIBES GOING WITH THE
ROLLING METHOD.
IT IS TOO HEAVY TO PICK UP.
>> ONE MORE ROLL.
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES HAVE TO
GET IT ON THE TRACK.
FAVORITE GOES FIRST.
FANS NOW GETTING THEIR ON THEIR
TRACK
MALCOLM IS GOING TO START
TOSSING TRYING TO GRAB THAT
PIECE OF MISSING TRACK.
JUST MISSES.
REYNOLD TRYING TO SECURE THAT
FIRST PIECE OF TRACK FOR FANS.
REYNOLD HAS IT.
EVERYBODY GOT TO PULL.
FANS HAVE THEIR FIRST SECTION TO
TRACK.
FAVORITES STILL LOOKING FOR THAT
FIRST SEC TO TRAP.
PHILLIP NOW TOSSING FOR THE
FAVORITES.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP HAS THE FIRST
SECTION FOR THE FAVORITES!
PULL!
FAVORITES HAVE THEIR FIRST
SECTION.
EDDIE NOW TOSSING FOR THE FANS.
EDDIE RIGHT THERE, JUST CAN'T DO
IT.
BOTH TRIBES NOW LOOKING FOR THAT
SECOND SECTION.
QUICKLY, MALCOLM HAS THE SECOND
SECTION FOR THE FAVORITES.
FAVORITES NOW IN THE LEAD.
>> ONE TWO, THREE!
>> Jeff: GO!
FANS NOW TRYING TO CATCH UP.
SHAMAR IS NOW TOSSING.
SHAMAR HAS THE SECOND SECTION
FOR THE FANS.
GO, FANS!
GO!
BOTH TRIBES NOW LOOKING FOR THAT
THIRD AND FINAL SECTION OF
TRACK.
IT'S BRANDON AND EDDIE NOW IN A
SHOWDOWN.
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE.
BRANDON VERY CLOSE.
JUST MISSING FOR THE FAVORITE.
EDDIE VERY CLOSE, CAN'T DO IT.
>> YOU'RE TOO EXCITED, MAN!
CALM DOWN!
>> Jeff: IT HAS BEEN BACK AND
FORTH IN THIS CHALLENGE.
AND IT'S COMING DOWN TO ONE LAST
TOSS.
>> FLIP IT.
>> Jeff: BRANDON VERY CLOSE.
TRIES TO FLIP IT AND JUST MISSES
AGAIN.
THIS CAN DO IT FOR THE FANS IF
HE CAN WORK IT.
JUST MISSES AGAIN
>> EASY, EASY.
>> Jeff: BRANDON IS RIGHT ON
IT.
THIS COULD DO IT FOR THE
FAVORITES RIGHT HERE.
BOTH GUYS VERY CLOSE.
>> EASY
>> PULL!
>> Jeff: BRANDON HAS IT FOR
THE FAVORITES!
EDDIE'S GOT TO PICK UP THE PACE
RIGHT NOW!
>> OH!
>> Jeff: JUST MISSES.
FANS NEED TO HOOK IT RIGHT HERE
TO HAVE ANY SHOT.
THAT'S IT.
FAVORITES WIN IMMUNITY AND
REWARD!
( CHEERS )
WELL, THIS CHALLENGE WAS NECK
AND NECK FROM THE START BUT ONTO
ONE TRIBE CAN WIN.
FAVORITES, CONGRATULATIONS.
COME GET YOUR REWARD.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
ALL RIGHT, FANS.
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU EXCEPT A
DATE WITH ME TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
THE THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
TRYING TO PAT OURSELVES ON THE
BACK IN ANY WAY BECAUSE WE LOST
AND WE HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL NOW.
>> YEAH, AND SHAMAR, I'M NOT
DISCREDITING--
>> DON'T TALK TO ME.
I SAID I HAVE CONTACT I NEED
THE GOGGLES.
YOU LOOK AT ME AND KEPT GOING.
THAT WAS DISRESPECTFUL.
I THINK THAT WAS DISGUSTING.
>> IF YOU NEEDED GOGGLES--
>> I SAID I NEEDED GOGGLES AND
YOU BROUGHT THEM DOWN AND YOU
TOOK THEM.
>> THIS ISN'T WHY WE LOST.
YOU DISGUST ME.
>> SHAMAR GOES OFF IN HIS
STUBBORN SHAMAR WAY AND CURSES
ME AND CALLS ME NAMES.
HE IS LESS MATURE THAN MY NEPHEW
GRAYSON AND MY NEPHEW IS THREE.
THIS GUY IS RIDICULOUS.
>> I KNOW.
>> JUST WHEN I THINK HE CAN'T
GET ANY MORE CHILDISH AND HE
DOES.
>> HOW MUCH DOES SHE HAVE TO DO
FOR THEM TO SAY ENOUGH IS ENOUGH
LET'S JUST VOTE HIM OUT.
>> I'M HERE BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO START THROWING MY NAME
OUT.
I SUCKED AT TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
I STARTED DOING BACKSTROKE IN
THE WRONG DIRECTION.
IT WAS AWFUL.
THE SWIMMING PART I JUST
COULDN'T--
>> IN THIS CHALLENGE, I BLEW IT.
I COULDN'T SWIM AS FAST AS
EVERYBODY ELSE.
FRANKLY, IT WAS PATHETIC, AND I
KNOW IT WAS, BUT THAT ALSO MEANS
OF THE THREE THAT ARE ON THE
OUTS RIGHT NOW, WE NEED TO KEEP
REYNOLD AND EDDIE AS LONG AS
POSSIBLE TO WIN SOME OF THESE
CHALANGES THAT'S WHY TONIGHT IT
SHOULD BE HOPE.
IF THIS GAME WERE ABOUT PHYSICAL
STRENGTH, THEY'D BE LOOKING AT
ME.
>> HOPE IS A SWEETHEART,
OBVIOUSLY, BUT IT'S NOT ABOUT
THAT.
REYNOLD IS HARD CORE GOOD IN THE
CHALLENGES.
>> WE NEED THEM.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
WE NEED EDDIE AND REYNOLD.
>> THEN THEY CAN GIVE THE IDOL
TO HOPE.
>> I DON'T TRUST HER.
LET'S SAY WE SPLIT VOTES BETWEEN
HOPE AND EDDIE AND THE FINAL
VOTE, WHEN WE REVOTE WILL BE FOR
HOPE DO WE WANT TO SAY GIRLS
VOTE FOR HOPE, BOYS VOTE FOR
EDDIE AND MAKE IT SIMPLE?
WE HAVE THREE GIRLS, THREE BOYS.
>> BOYS ARE VOTING FOR EDDIE.
GIRLS ARE VOTING FOR HOPE.
THEY'RE TRYING TO FLUSH OUT THE
IDOL.
SO WE NEED THREE EDDIE, THREE
HOPE.
IF THEY PLAY THE IDOL, THEN THE
IDOL COMES OUT.
AND WE KNOW WHERE IT IS.
>> BUT THEN THERE ARE GOING TO
BE THREE EDDIE, THREE HOPE, AND
THREE ME.
>> I AM THE ONE WHO IS
CONTROLLING SHAMAR.
I'M KEEPING HIM CALM.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO I JUST VOTE FOR
WHO?
>> EDDIE.
>> I JUST NEED SHAMAR TO KEEP
HIS MOUTH SHUT UNTIL WE ONE BY
ONE KNOCK THEM OUT.
REYNOLD, EDDIE AND HOPE.
HOPEFULLY IT'S HOPE TONIGHT.
>> IT'S NOT A GOOD FEELING ROORK
RIGHT, WHEN YOU KNOW YOU DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING WRONG BUT EVERYBODY
WANTS TO GET YOU, RIGHT?
I'VE BEEN THERE.
( LAUGHS )
>> YEAH--
>> IT'S NOT THE BEST FEELING.
I'M JUST TRYING TO ENJOY MY LAST
LITTLE MOMENT.
YOU KNOW, I'M CONCERNED I'M ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK TONIGHT.
REYNOLD IS SAFE BECAUSE HE HAS
THE IDOL.
I CAN'T SEE HIM GIVING UP HIS
IDOL BECAUSE IT'S SUCH A RISKY
MOVE.
>> IF IT I WAS UP TO ME, IT
WOULD BE DIFFERENT, I WOULD TAKE
HIM OUT.
BUT HE HAS THAT NECKLACE.
TRUST ME, I WOULD MUCH RATHER
YOU STAY.
YOU'RE NOT 99% IN THE HOLE.
I'LL BE HONEST, I'M NOT VOTING
FOR YOU TONIGHT.
>> WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S OUT OF MY
CONTROL NOW.
>> YOU CAN ALWAYS THROW THE
VOTE.
A DIFFERENT WAY.
YOU COULD ALWAYS VOTE FOR ONE OF
THOSE GUYS, YOU KNOW?
THAT'S ALL I'M GOING TO TELL
YOU.
IT DEPENDS ON WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO, WHICH WAY YOU WANT TO GO.
WHEN HOPE CAME DOWN TO THE
WATER, I KIND OF-- YOU KNOW, I
GET ALONG WITH HER BETTER THAN I
GET ALONG WITH EDDIE AND
REYNOLD, SO I NATURALLY WANT HER
TO STAY, AND SO-- LIKE I TRIED
TO GIVE HER A HINT ON WHAT WOULD
SAVE HER FATE.
AFTER YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENS
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M
SAYING.
WE'RE GOING TO SPLIT THE VOTE
TONIGHT BETWEEN HER AND EDDIE,
SO I BASICALLY KIND OF SAID,
LIKE, ALL SHE HAS TO DO IS VOTE
UNDER EDDIE TO SAVE HERSELF.
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF SHE'S REALLY
GOING TO TAKE HEED.
>> I TALKED TO SHAMAR.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND HE JUST MADE IT SOUND
LIKE IT WAS FOR SURE THE GROUP
HAD DECIDE IT WAS ME OR EDDIE
GOING HOME.
>> SHAMAR TOLD HOPE THE PLAN
THAT WE'RE DOING.
AND THEE JUST CAME TO ME.
>> THE ENTIRE PLAN.
>> YEP.
>> NOW HE IS NO LONGER IN THIS
GAME.
HE'S JUST ( BLEEP ).
SHAMAR DRIVES ME CRAZY IN EVERY
SENSE POSSIBLE.
>> AND COULDN'T BELIEVE THAT HE
BLURBED WHAT OUR PLAN WAS
BECAUSE I THINK HE DOESN'T CARE
ABOUT THE GAME.
SHAMAR JUST TOLD HOPE THAT-- OUR
PLAN.
YUP.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT BUT I CAN
BELIEVE IT THAT SHAMAR JUST
OPENED HIS MOUTH.
>> IF HE JUST TOLD HOPE THE PLAN
HE'S NOT PLANNING ON VOTING WITH
US, IS HE.
SHAMAR AT THIS POINT I BELIEVE
IS A COMPLETE WILD CARD.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT SHAMAR
NOT VOTING WITH US?
>> YUP.
>> OH, MY GOD, I'M SCARED.
I'M IN A PRETTY ROUGH SPOT
BECAUSE IF THOSE THREE DO HAVE
THE IDOL, I'M WORRIED IF
SOMETHING WERE TO GO WRONG, IT'S
PROBABLY MY NAME THAT'S ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> I CAN GET JULIA TO VOTE
SHAMAR TONIGHT.
>> RIGHT.
>> I CAN.
>> I'M REALLY CLOSE TO JULIA.
>> UH-HUH.
>> THERE'S THREE OF YOU AND
THERE'S TWO OF US.
THAT MAKES FIVE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND WE JUST NEED FIVE TO GET
THE VOTE.
I'M ABSOLUTELY IN.
TO GET SHAMAR TONIGHT.
>> YUP.
IF YOU CAN GAWRNLT-- IF YOU CAN
GET JULIA, I'M ON TEAM SHAMAR.
I'M GOING TO VOTE SHAMAR EVERY
DAY.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW I WANT HIM OUT.
THIS GAME HAS CHANGE FLAFTD
HOUR.
THE LATEST DEVELOPMENT WHICH I
HAVE A REALLY GOOD FEELING ABOUT
IS THAT SHAMAR IS GOING HOME.
I CAN GUARANTEE YOU THREE FOR
SHAMAR.
YOU HAVE TO GET THE OTHER TWO.
>> I'LL TALK TO THEM.
>> DO IT.
IT'S GOING TO BE GREAT.
THIS COULD BE EPIC, EPIC TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
EVERY GOES AWRY TONIGHT I MIGHT
HAVE TO PULL SOME CRAZY MOVES
WITH THE IDOL BUT HOPEFULLY WE
SEND SHAMAR PACKING TONIGHT.
IT WOULD BE LIKE CHRISTMAS.
>> Jeff: SO, REYNOLD, A LOT
WAS SAID AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WAS THERE ANY FALLOUT WHEN YOU
GUYS GOT BACK TO CAMP?
>> YEAH.
I DON'T RECALL ME DOING SO MUCH
YELLING BECAUSE I WAS CONFUSED.
I WAS SHOCKED.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT I HEARD SHAMAR SCREAMING
FROM, LIKE, A KILOMETER AWAY AT
EVERYBODY.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TFS ABOUT BUT
ON I WAS NOT SURPRISED.
IT'S PAR FOR THE COURSE FOR HIM.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, ONCE AGAIN ON
THE HOT SEAT, AND ALL IT
SURROUNDING YOUR TEMPER OR YOUR
ATTITUDE.
>> WELL, IT WASN'T A KILOMETER
AWAY.
I WAS YELLING AT HIM ABOUT HIM
BEING UPSET ABOUT HIS PLAN NOT
WORKING.
I DON'T KNOW, MY NAME COMES UP
WITH EVERYTHING.
I'M LIKE THE SCAP SCAPEGOAT FOR
EVERYBODY JUNK.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU OFTEN
MISUNDERSTOOD?
>> NOT THIS MUCH.
THESE PEOPLE PUT OUT CERTAIN
PERCEPTIONS.
WHEN YOU ARE DEALING WITH PEOPLE
WHO ARE LYING --
>> WHO HERE HAS LIED?
>> REYNOLD HAS LIED.
>> JEFF, I DON'T KNOW WHEN I
LIED TO SHAMAR BECAUSE HE HAS A
POLICY WHERE I'M NOT ATHROWD
TALK TO HIM.
>> BUT YOU STILL DO IT.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, YOU TOLD HIM,
JUST DON'T TALK TO ME.
>> BUT HE STILL DOES IT.
>> Jeff: IT IS A SOCIAL GAME.
>> EIGHT SOCIAL GAME AND HE'S
TRYING TO PLAY THAT ASPECT OF
THE GAME OH, I'M FRIENDLY TO
EVERYBODY AND HE DOESN'T WANT TO
TALK TO ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
DON'T PLAY THAT GAME WITH ME.
I THINK YOU'RE AN EVIL PERSON.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
>> Jeff: HOPE, WHAT'S YOUR
TAKE ON SHAMAR?
>> I SPOKE WITH SHAMAR TODAY IN
THE WATER, AND HE SAID IT'S 99%
SURE YOU'RE GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> THAT IS NOT TRUE.
>> HE SAID IF I WERE YOU, I
WOULD TURN ON YOUR FRIEND
BECAUSE REYNOLD IS NOT GOING TO
GIVE YOU THE IDOL.
>> YOU SAID YOU WERE GOING HOME
AND I SAID THAT'S NOT 99% TRUE.
EVERYBODY HERE IS LET'S THROW
SHAMAR UNDER THE BUS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I COME IN
SMILING AND MAKING JOKES IT'S
LIKE TO KEEP THE HEAT OFF OF ME,
JUST BLAME IT ON HIM.
I DON'T KNOW, IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> Jeff: MATT WHAT, IS IT
ABOUT SHAMAR THAT HE FEELS VERY
PICKED ON.
HE FEELS LIKE, "WHY ME?"
>> I THINK SHAMAR GETS A LITTLE
CARRIED AWAY WITH HIS ATTITUDE,
AND SEEMS TO GET AGGRAVATED REAL
EASILY.
AND I THINK HIS PERSONALITY IS
JUST KIND OF RUBBING PEOPLE IN
THE TRIBE THE WRONG WAY.
>> Jeff: JULIA, THE ENTIRE
TIME MATT WAS TALKING YOU WERE
RELIVING A TRAUMA JUST SHAKING
YOUR HEAD?
>> YES, AFTER THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
HE FELT ATTACKED AND WANTED TO
JUSTIFY WHAT WE HAD SAID AT
TRIBAL AND HE SCREAMED AT ME
AGAIN, AGAIN AND AGAIN.
"YOU'RE WEAK.
YOU'RE A WEAK PERSONALITY AND
PROJECTING IT ON TO ME."
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, THAT DID NOT
HAPPEN, EITHER?
>> NO.
>> AND THAT'S THE ESSENCE OF THE
PROBLEM.
PEOPLE TAKE WHAT I SAY AND
EMBELLISH THEM BECAUSE THEY FEEL
A CERTAIN WAY.
AND I CAN'T DO ANYTHING ABOUT
THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> Jeff: SO FAR JUST IN A FEW
MINUTE, SHAMAR, YOU'VE HAD A
BEEF WITH JULIA, MATT, HOPE, AND
REYNOLD.
>> AND HAVEN'T TALKED TO SHERRI
OR MICHAEL.
>> ASK THEM.
>> Jeff: SHERRI, WHY IS IT
THIS ONE GUY IS TAKING ALL THE
HEAT WHEN HE SAYS, "I'M NOT
DOING ANYTHING?"
>> OKAY, SHAMAR-- I'VE MET LOTS
OF SHAMARS.
I GET SHAMAR.
HE JUST RUBS THEM THE WRONG WAY,
AND ONCE YOU CROSS HIM, YOU JUST
CAN'T GO BACK.
AND THEY CROSSED HIM.
IN HIS MIND, THAT'S IT.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
>> Jeff: OKAY, SO, THE OTHER
BIG THING GOING ON IN THIS TRIBE
IS WHAT CAME OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND THAT'S
REYNOLD AND HOPE AND EDDIE AND
ALLIE, WHO WAS VOTED OUT, BEING
THIS SORT OF FOURSOME.
SO, HOPE, ARE YOU CONCERNED
ABOUT TONIGHT'S VOTE?
>> ABSOLUTE.
I MEAN, AFTER LAST TRIBAL I
WOULD SAY I WOULD BE NEXT ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> Jeff: SO IF IT'S NOT YOU,
WHO WOULD YOU PUT THE VOTE ON
HONESTLY, I HATE TO GO
BACK TO SHAMAR BUT I JUST FEEL
LIKE HE BRINGS A LOT OF NEGATIVE
ENERGY TO THE TRIBE AND I JUST
DON'T REALLY SEE IT CHANGE THRAG
MUCH.
SO...
>> Jeff: AND, EDDIE, CONCERNED
AFTER THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL
THAT THEY LOOK AT AND YOU THINK
HE'S FLIRTING WITH HOPE.
HE'S ALIGNED WITH REYNOLD.
HE'S TOO CHARMING, AND HE'S TOO
FIT.
WE CAN'T LET HIM LAST.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I ABSOLUTELY
FEEL LIKE I HAVE BEEN WEARING A
TARGET ON MY BACK FOR QUITE SOME
TIME NOW.
>> Jeff: DID YOU GET VOTES
LAST NAME TIME?
>> I DID NOT GET VOTES LAST TIME
BUT SHAMAR HAS BEEN TRYING TO
GET ME OUT SINCE DAY ONE WHICH I
HAVE BEEN DOING TO HIM.
SHAMAR HATE ME AS MUCH AS
REYNOLD.
I'M NOT ALLOWEDDED TO TALK TO
HIM AT CAMP.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE ON THE
NO-TALKING LIST.
>> THE REASON I PUT YOU ON THE
NO-TALKING LIST IS YOU'RE A
FOLLOWER TO THE REAL PERSON I
DON'T LIKE.
SO THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, HOW BIG A
FACTOR IS THE IDOL.
LAST TRIBAL YOU WERE VERY OPEN--
"HERE IT IS, I'M GOING TO PLAY
IT TONIGHT, AND "AND PSYCHE YOU
DIDN'T PLAY IT.
>> YEAH, IT'S GOING TO BE A
POKER GAME FROM HERE UNTIL IT'S
EVENTUALLY PLAYED POUR I GET
VOTED OUT OR WHAT HAVE YOU.
IT'S A POKER GAME.
>> Jeff: WITH THAT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
MICHAEL, YOU'RE UP.
>> THANKS FOR SERVING OUR
COUNTRY.
GOOD LUCK
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THEVOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SHAMAR.
HOPE.
SHAMAR.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES SHAM ATWO
VOTES HOPE.
SHAMAR.
THREE VOTES SHAMAR.
HOPE.
TIED AGAIN.
THREE VOTES SHAMAR, THREE VOTES
HOPE.
EDDIE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES SHAMAR, THREE
VOTES HOPE, ONE VOTE EDDIE.
EDDIE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES SHAM THREE
VOTES HOPE, TWO VOTES EDDIE, ONE
VOTE LEFT.
EDDIE.
WE HAVE A THREE-WAY TIE.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN.
WE'RE GOING TO REVOTE.
YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR HOPE,
EDDIE, OR SHAMAR, AND HOPE,
EDDIE, AND SHAMAR, YOU WILL NOT
VOTE.
MICHAEL, IF YOU'RE TAKE THIS
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE.
SHAMAR.
HOPE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES HOPE, ONE VOTE
SHAMAR.
HOPE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES HOPE, ONE
VOTE SHAMAR.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: FANS VERSUS
FAVORITE," HOPE, THAT'S FOUR,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
HOPE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, THERE ARE TWO WAYS TO LOOK
AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ONE AS A SIGN OF WHAT'S TO COME,
MORE DYSFUNCTION.
OR, TWO, AS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
CHANGE YOUR STORY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"."
>> WHERE DO YOU THINK WE'RE
GOING TO GO FROM HERE NOW?
>> Jeff: THE FANS THINK
THEY'VE HIT ROCK BOTTOM.
>> DIDN'T YOU SAY I WANT THE
STRONGEST TEAM POSSIBLE.
>> YES, I SAID THAT!
YES, I SAID THAT!
>> Jeff: BUT NATURE PROVES
THEM WRONG.
>> HURRICANE.
NOW THE RATS.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M REALLY, REALLY
DISAPPOINTED.
I DEFINITELY THINK THAT, YOU
KNOW, I SHOULD HAVE STAYED OUT
HERE LONGER.
I THOUGHT I WAS A STRONG PLAYER.
AND I FEEL LIKE I'M LEAVING
BEFORE MY TIME, BUT I WILL SAY
THAT THIS HAS BEEN AN
INCREDIBLE, ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
EXPERIENCE.
>> AND FEEL REALLY GRATEFUL, YOU
KNOW, FOR HAVING THE
OPPORTUNITY.