>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE SWITCHING TRIBES.
>> OH, MAN!
>> Jeff: AT THE NEW BIKAL
TRIBE, THE FAVORITES HAD A
NUMBERS ADVANTAGE OVER THE FANS,
BUT IT COULDN'T MEND AN OLD FEUD
BETWEEN PHILLIP AND CORINNE.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO DUMP PHILLIP
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> CORINNE CONSISTENTLY HAS
CONVERSATIONS WITH MICHAEL AND
FOR ME THAT'S UB ACCEPTABLE.
>> Jeff: WHILE THE NEW GOTA
TRIBE WAS RIDING HIGH, MALCOLM
WAS GATHERING INFORMATION--
>> I HAVE THE IDOL.
>> Jeff:... TO PLOT HIS NEXT
MOVE ALONGSIDE EDDIE, ERIK, AND
REYNOLD.
>> I WANT TO SPEARHEAD HAVING
THESE FOUR GUYS JOIN FORCES.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, GOTA CONTINUED THEIR
IMPRESSIVE WINNING STREAK.
GOTA WINS IMMUNITY!
AFTER PHILLIP DIDN'T DELIVER A
WIN FOR BIKAL, HE CLAIMED LOSING
WAS ALL PART OF HIS PLAN TO TAKE
OUT JEWEL YARK THE WEAKEST OF
THE FANS.
>> I MEAN, IT'S COMPLETE CRAP.
THIS IS COMPLIET A LIE.
>> WE'RE STILL ON WITH
SPLITTING, RIGHT?
>> THERE'S NO POINT SPLITTING
THE VOTE.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE HE TRUSTS
US.
>> Jeff: BUT PHILLIP'S FEUD
WITH CORINNE--
>> I HAVE THE NUMBERS WITHOUT
HIM.
>> Jeff:... MADE HIM CONSIDER
TAKING OUT HER NEW ALLY,
MICHAEL.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, BIKAL WENT
ALONG WITH CORINNE AND
UNANIMOUSLY VOTE OUT THEIR
WEAKEST MEMBER.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUR THE
REQUEST 9 SURVIVOR: FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES," JULIA.
JULIA, THE DESCRIBE OF TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
12 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> MICHAEL, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I'M SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
THANK YOU.
>> A TRUE SURVIVOR.
>> KNOW IT WAS HARD PROBABLY TO
SEE JULIA GO.
IT WAS HER OR YOU, SO... TRIBAL
WAS THIS THIS WHOLE RIGAMAROLE
OF SPLITTING VOTE, BUT OBVIOUSLY
I DID MY JOB.
I MADE SURE MICHAEL STAYED.
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
AND SO MICHAEL'S MINE.
>> I'M SO HAPPY.
>> CONGRATS, BABY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SORRY.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN PHILLIP PULLS
DAWN AND I ASIDE LIKE AN
A.D.D. KID.
HE CAN'T WAIT, HE'S GOT
SOMETHING HE WANTS TO SAY.
>> THERE WAS ONE THING WE DIDN'T
THAT I DIDN'T CLUE YOU IN ON.
>> WHAT.
>> I THREW THE CHALLENGE TODAY.
>> NO WAY.
>> DI.
>> WOW.
>> COCHRAN KNEW ABOUT IT, BUT
BASICALLY YOU NOTICED WHAT I WAS
DOING BUT YOU DIDN'T FIGURE IT
OUT.
YOU SAID, "PHILLIP, PULL THE
LINE IN QUICKER."
REMEMBER THAT "PULL THE LINE IN
QUICKER."
I WASN'T PULLING IT IN QUICKER.
>> THERE WAS NO POINT IN SAYING,
"PHILLIP I KNOW YOU DIDN'T THROW
THE CHALLENGE."
LIKE I WOULD SAY TO A NORMAL
PERSON, "YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
YOU DIDN'T THROW THE CHALLENGE.
IT WAS THE BIGGEST JOKE OF THE
YEAR.
>> IT WAS TOUGH FOR ME TO DO
THAT AS A COMPETITOR BUT I
THOUGHT THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
I'M WALKING OVER THERE WITH
HAVING ONLY GOTTEN RID OF ONE
PERSON.
>> YOU COULD HAVE JUST TOLD US.
WE WOULD HAVE SAID OKAY.
>> WHEN I ACTUALLY MADE THE
DECISION IT WASN'T BEFORE.
IT HAPPENED IN THE GAME AND I
WAS LIKE, GO FOR IT.
I KNEW YOU GUYS WERE GOING TO
WANT ME TO DO THAT.
>> AT THE CHALLENGE.
THAT'S CONVENIENT.
THAT'S AROUND THE SAME TIME THAT
YOU BLEW THE CHALLENGE.
>> I JUST DON'T BELIEVE IT.
LIKE JUST SAY, "I SCREWED UP ON
THE CHALLENGE."
IT'S ANNOYING.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
IT'S, LIKE, REALLY EMBARRASSING
FOR HIM.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S TIMES LIKE THESE WHERE
YOU'RE LIKE, YES, HE'S A LOYAL
ALLIANCE MEMBER BUT HE'S SO
CUCKOO FOR COCOA PUFFS, THERE'S
NO QUESTION PHILLIP HAS TO GO.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S A NICE
LUXURY?
I DON'T THINK THAT MOST OF THE
FANS HAVE A BRAIN.
I THINK ONLY MICHAEL DOES.
I DON'T THINK SHERRI, EDDIE, AND
REYNOLD.
>> CAN'T JUDGE THEM UNTIL I GET
AROUND THEM.
>> THEY'RE NOT SAVVY PLAYERS.
IT'S REMARKABLE.
>> WE ALL GET TOGETHER, TRY TO
AVIED ANY ONE-OFF CONVERSATIONS
BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING TO BE
LOOKING.
WE'VE GOT A BEAUTIFUL THING
GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
I JUST WANT TO BE SURE OUR
ALLIANCE IS HYPER VILL JANT.
BUT KEEPING IT FUN.
>> IT'S DAY 20 AND WE'RE
ANTICIPATING A MERGE SOME TIME
SOON.
I TRIED REALLY HARD TO PLAY THIS
TIME LIKE IT'S A BRAND NEW GAME
BUT THIS IS ABOUT THE POINT
WHERE LAST TIME THE GAME FELL
APART FOR ME REALLY WITHIN A
TWO-DAY TIME PERIOD, COCHRAN HAD
FLIPPED AND EVERYTHING CHANGE.
I'M GOING TO GO TO THE WELL.
I THINK IT WILL BE GOOD FOR ME.
>> YOU WANT TO GO BY YOURSELF.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU SURE?
>> IT IS KIND OF FUNNY THAT I
CRY SO MUCH.
BUT IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE NOT
TO CRY WHEN I THINK WHAT A
MILLION DOLLARS CAN DO FOR MY
FAMILY.
I HAVE SIX CHILDREN.
I MEAN, THAT'S COLLEGE.
THAT'S LIFE CHANGING FOR THEIR
FUTURE.
THERE'S SO MUCH ON THE LINE.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE I DON'T SIT
BACK.
LAST TIME I LET MY GAME GO TO
HECK.
I LET COCHRAN FLIP.
I DIDN'T TELL ANYONE.
I DIDN'T CHANGE, LIKE, THE
OUTCOME FOR ME.
LIKE YOU NEED TO BE A DECISION
MAKENER THIS GAME.
YOU CAN'T LET THE GAME HAPPEN TO
YOU.
YOU HAVE TO BE THE ONE THAT
MAKES THE DECISIONS.
THOSE ARE THE PEOPLE THAT WIN.
>> THERE'S A BIG BOAT COMING
TOWARDS US.
>> WHAT?
>> THERE'S A BOAT COMING ASHORE.
>> IT'S A BOAT AND IT'S TURNING!
>> SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WE'VE BEEN SAVED!
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT SOMETHING AWESOME IS ABOUT
TO HAPPEN.
THESE COOL DIEWDZ IN THEIR
VINCENT BOAT JUST PULLED UP.
>> GET ME OFF OF THIS ISLAND!
>> DO YOU SPEAK ENGLISH?
>> HE'S GOT A NOTE.
OH, MY GOD.
READ IT.
>> GOTA TRIBE, GATHER UP
EVERYTHING YOU NEED FOR THE
REMAINDER OF YOUR TIME IN
CARAMMON PUP WILL NEED THIS KEY
WHEN YOU ARRIVE AT YOUR NEW
HOME!
( CHEERS )
THE NOTE SAYS A NEW HOME.
SO WE'RE THINKING MERGE TIME,
BABY.
>> AWESOME!
>> WE LOAD UP THE BOAT.
>> I'M READY TO GET BACK WITH
THE OLD FAVORITES, PHILLIP,
COCHRAN, DAWN.
I HAVEN'T SEEN THEM FAIR WHILE.
NOW THAT IT'S AN INDIVIDUAL GAME
I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT EVERYBODY.
IT'S EXCITING BUT I HAVE TO BE
ON MY TOES.
>> ONWARD AND UPWARDS.
>> OH, MY GOD!
NO WAY, YOU GUYS!
>> SEEING THE BOAT COMING AND
THAT THE MERGE HAD ARRIVED IS
ALWAYS THE PART OF THE GAME I'M
MOST EXCITED ABOUT
( APPLAUSE )
>> IT WAS LIKE AN AWESOME MOMENT
TO THAN YOU'VE ACTUALLY MADE THE
MERGE AND ALL THESE PEOPLE THAT
YOU HAVEN'T MET THUS FAR ARE
GOING TO BE INJECTED INTO GAME
WITH YOU WHICH IS KIND OF NICE
BECAUSE YOU'RE REALLY SICK OF
TALKING TO THE SAME PEOPLE OVER
AND OVER AGAIN.
>> WELCOME ABOARD.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF
WELCOMING WE WERE GOING TO
RECEIVE BUT IT WAS LIKE
EVERYBODY RAN ON THE BEACH.
IT FELT LIKE FRIENDS,UN.
>> WELCOME TO THE OTHER BEACH!
>> IT'S IRONIC, BECAUSE WE'VE
BEEN SO AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS,
FANS VERSUS FAVORITES BUT THEY
GAVE US A NEW OF NICE WARM
WELCOME.
>> READ THE NOTE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> LET'S OPEN THAT THING
ALREADY.
>> OOOH!
( APPLAUSE )
>> GREEN, BABY.
>> ALL RIGHT, US.
GREEN!
>> YEAH, I LOVE IT.
>> THE FIRST THING WE DO, OF
COURSE IS GO RIGHT FOR THE FOOD.
SO THE FOOD GOES DOWN, AND DAWN
GOES INTO MOM MODE AND STARTS
MAKING SANDWICHES, CUTTING THE
CHEESE.
LITERALLY CUTTING THE CHEESE.
>> I'M SO HAPPY TO BE HERE
TODAY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, EVERYBODY.
>> YEAH.
>> ESPECIALLY YOU GUYS HAD SUCH
A HARD FIRST HALF OF THE GAME.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING?
SEVEN LOSSES IN A ROW?
NO BIG DEAL.
>> WE'RE ALL WITH EACH OTHER
NOW.
>> DO WE KNOW OUR NAME?
>> I THINK WE SHOULD WITH
STANLEY.
>> WE WERE LIKE WHAT IF WE
CALLED IT DOUGLAS.
>> ENIL DAME MEANS NEW
BEGINNING.
>> EVERYONE IS COOL WITH THAT
NAME?
>> I'M OKAY WITH THAT.
>> IT HAS A NICE RING TO IT.
>> THE FACT THE OF THE MATTER
SIJUST WANTED TO NAME THE TRIBE
AFTER MY MOM, HER NAME IS
MADELEINE, AND IT'S MADELEINE
BACKGROUNDS.
>> IT'S ENIL ADAM.
I MAY BE BUTCHERING IT.
THIS IS THE DUMBEST NAME EVER,
AND IT HAS TOO MANY SYLLABLE
>> FRAUM, I WANT MY HUG.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> IT'S GOOD TO SEE MY GIRL.
>> I KNOW.
>> OKAY, I BELIEF IN MY PEEPS.
WE KNOW FAVORITE HAVE TO GO ALL
THE WAY.
WHAT HAPPENS AFTER SIX, WE DON'T
BUT WE KNOW HOW TO PLAY THIS
GAME.
I CAN TELL YOU RIGHT NOW,
COCHRAN, MYSELF, DAUN-- AND ME.
>> TIGHT TOWER.
>> IT'S A TIGHT FOUR.
WHEN YOU'RE LAYING IN BED
TONIGHT PRETEND YOU'RE BOSTON
ROB.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
WE CAN WIN.
THP ONE OF US FOUR COULD WIN IT.
IT WOULD BE TOUGH BUT IT MEANS
MAKE SOMETHING STREAKIC MOVES AT
THE RIGHT TIME.
AS LONG AS THE POWERFUL MEN FROM
THE FANS GOES FIRST--
>> YES.
>> ONE THING I KNOW ABOUT
CORINNE IS THAT THE PEOPLE THAT
SHE WOULD TRY TO GO TO NOW WOULD
BE THE FANS BUT SHE WOULDN'T DO
IT TOO SOON.
>> TO ME, PERSONALLY, THIS FIRST
VOTE... IT'S NOT A HUGE DEAL.
I MEAN, THERE'S EIGHT FAVORITES
AND FOUR FANS, SO I FEEL SECURE
IN MY ALLIANCE AND MY ALLIANCE
WITHIN AN ALLIANCE BUT IT'S A
LOT SCARIER NOW BECAUSE IT'S
INDIVIDUAL AND PEOPLE START
GETTING HUNGRIER AND THEY WANT
TO START MAKING MOVES AND THIS
IS THE TIME.
THIS IS WHEN PEOPLE START
SCRAMBLING, AND IN SCRAMBLES,
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
>> MALCOLM, YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
HE WAS AWFUL TO ME.
IT WAS LIKE THE CRAZY PHILLIP
FROM THE OTHER SEASON TIMES 10.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH
HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> HE WAS NASTY TO ME.
AT ONE POINT I WAS LIKE,... TAKE
PHILLIP OUT.
>> I DON'T PLAN ON SITTING
AROUND FOR A LONG TIME.
>> HOW DO WE WORK THIS.
THERE WERE NOT ENOUGH MEMBERS OF
US.
>> REYNOLD AND EDDIE ARE
COMPLETELY IN MY POCK.
>> ERIK FLOATS AROUND BUT HE'S
ON BOARD WITH THE GUYS.
>> I'VE GOT MICHAEL.
>> THAT'S SIX.
>> I HAVEN'T LIKED THIS PASSIVE
PLODDING ALONG GAME I'VE BEEN
PLAYING WITH THE FAVORITES.
AND I'VE BEEN LOOKING TO MAKE MY
MOVE.
WE HAVE A VERY FRAGILE
SIX-PERSON ALLIANCE THAT THE
EXPOINT THERE ARE 12 PEOPLE LEFT
IN THIS GAME.
THAT'S NOT A CLEAR-CUT MAJORITY.
IF WE CAN GET THROUGH ONE VOTE
AND KEEP OUR NUMBERS INTACT THEN
WE HAVE THE ULTIMATE POWER TO DO
WHAT WE WANT.
>> I FEEL LIKE SHERRI IS THE
EASIEST PERSON.
>> SHE'S WEIRD.
YOU'LL SEE.
IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE DEALING WITH
HER.
>> IF WE TAKE SHERRI OUT FIRST
AND THEN PHILLIP.
HE'S THE HEAD OF THIS NONSENSE.
AS LONG AS PHILLIP GOES, THE
WHOLE ORGANIZATION WILL CRUMBLE.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
THE MOST AMAZING THING ABOUT
MALCOLM IN A FIVE-MINUTE
DOWNLOAD WE CAN GET ON THE SAME
PAGE.
HE'S LIKE I HAVE REYNOLD AND
EDDIE.
DO YOU HAVE MIKE SNELL AND I'M
LIKE, YUP, MICHAEL IS MINE.
OH, MY GOD.
THANK GOD FOR MALCOLM.
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE TOGETHER ON
THE FIRST VOTE AND BLINDSIDE THE
FAVORITES.
I'VE YET TO BE INVOLVED IN A
BLINDSIDE.
IT'S TIME.
BLINDSIDE TIME.
>> "CAN YOU STOMACH THE STRESS
OF TRIBAL COUNCIL?
HAVE YOU BITTEN OFF MORE THAN
YOU CAN CHEW?"
>> YES!
>> "SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE AND A
WHOLE LOT MORE."
>> YES!
>> "OR BY THIS EVENING YOU COULD
BE THROUGH."
>> EATING THINGS?
>> .
>> NO, GROSS.
>> BUGS, TARANTULAS, WORMS.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I'M REALLY NOT LOOKING IN
ORDER TO THIS.
>> TREE MAIL COMES AND WHAT IS
IT, MY ONE WEAKNESS-- EATING
DISGUSTING STUFF.
IT IS GOING TO BE A TRUE TEST,
AND I GUESS IT'S FITTING.
THE TIME I NEED IT THE MOST,
PERSONAL IMMUNITY, IT'S GOING TO
BE THE THING THAT'S HARDEST FOR
ME.
>> THE WORST PART IS WHEN YOU GO
HOME AND LIKE YOU'RE ABOUT TO
HOOK UP WITH THE CHICK'S AND
THEY'RE LIKE DIDN'T YOU EAT A
COW'S... OR SOMETHING.
>> HE IS WORRIED IT MIGHT DAMAGE
HIS DATING PROSPECT, THAT HE
PARTOOK IN SOMETHING GROSS,
PARTICULARLY ALIENATING WOMEN.
FOR ME I NEED A REHABILITATION.
IT MIGHT ADD A WILD STREAK TO ME
AND MAKE ME LOOK A LITTLE MORE
TRUSS.
I THINK THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT MY
LOVE LIFE NEEDS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
ANDREA.
GET RID OF THIS.
>> INDIVIDUAL N-
>> Jeff: TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NO
MORE.
>> NO MAS.
>> Jeff: INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
IS WHAT YOU COVET.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU WILL TAKE PART IN A
"SURVIVOR" CLASSIC.
IT'S A FOOD-EATING COMPETITION
WHERE YOU WILL RACE TO GET DOWN
LOCAL DELICACIES.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: IT WON'T ALWAYS BE
PLEASANT.
THEY WON'T ALWAYS BE FAMILIAR
BUT THESE ARE THINGS THAT ARE
EATEN OUT HERE EVERY DAY.
YOU'LL SQUARE OFF IN A SERIES OF
ELIMINATION ROUNDS UNTIL ONLY
TWO REMAIN.
WINNER GETS THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE SSAFE AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
EVERYBODY ELSE GETS TO TRIBAL
VULNERABLE, AND SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTEDLY OUT TONIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO DRAW FOR
POSITIONS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> I'M SO NERVOUS!
>> COME ON, CORINNE!
SUCK IT UP!
>> MINE MOVED A LITTLE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE
OUR FIRST ROUND OF SIX.
ANDREA, SHERRI, CORINNE, ERIK,
EDDIE, AND MALCOLM.
THE FIRST THREE TO FINISH WILL
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
LET'S REVEAL AND SEE WHAT YOU'RE
EATING
>> IT'S MOVING.
>> Jeff: THIS IS BEATLE LARVA.
>> IT'S RUNNING OFF THE PLATE.
>> Jeff: THIS TAKES US BACK TO
SEASON ONE, FIRST TIME WE DID
THIS.
>> I'M GOING TO BE SICK.
>> IS IT GOING TO BITE ME?
>> Jeff: FIRST THREE TO FINISH
MOVE ON.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY THROWING
THEM IN, NOBODY MESSING AROUND.
>> GO CORINNE.
>> Jeff: SHOW ME AN EMPTY
MOUTH WHEN YOU'RE DONE,
COMPLETELY EMPTY.
ANDREA'S GOOD, THAT'S ONE.
LOOKING FOR TWO MORE TO MOVE ON.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
MALCOLM IS IN.
>> NICE!
>> COME ON, COME ON!
>> Jeff: ONE SPOT LEFT.
EDDIE IS IN, THAT'S IT.
SHER EERK CORINNE, AND ERIK ARE
OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE JUST LIKE
THAT
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE
OUR NEXT ROUND-- REYNOLD,
BRENDA, PHILLIP, MICHAEL, COCK
EXPRAN DAUN.
YOU'RE EATING THE SAME THING THE
FIRST SIX ATE.
REVEAL.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: MORE BEATLE LARVAE.
>> WAIT, YOU HAVE TO PUT YOUR
HANDS DOWN.
NOT YET.
>> CAN I GO WHOLE.
>> Jeff: DAWN PUT YOUR FOOD
DOWN.
>> DON'T CALL IT FOOD.
>> PUT IT DOWN?
>> Jeff: JUST WAIT.
>> FOR?
EVERYBODY PUT YOUR
HANDS ON THE
TABLE.
THREE MORE FROM THIS ROUND WILL
MOVE ON.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> COME ON DAWN, YOU'VE GOT IT.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT TO SHOW ME
AN EMPTY MOUTH.
>> CHEW, CHEW, CHEW, CHEW, CHEW.
ENJOY IT.
COCHRAN, LIKE THAT.
>> WOW!
PHILLIP, ONE SPOT LEFT.
DAWN LOOKING FOR IT, MICHAEL,
BRENDA, REYNOLD, WHO'S GOING TO
JOIN PHILLIP AND COCHRAN?
MICHAELS THAT.
MOVING ON
KEEP IT DOWN!
THERE IT IS!
MICHAEL, PHILLIP, AND COCHRAN
MOVING ON.
DAWN, BRENDA AND REYNOLD OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
>> SO DISGUSTING!
>> Jeff: JUST LIKE THAT WE ARE
DOWN TO SIX.
ANDREA, COCHRAN, PHILLIP,
MICHAEL, EDDIE, AND MALCOLM.
THREE OF YOU WILL MOVE ON TO THE
NEXT ROUND.
REVEAL.
WHEES LOOETS SEE WHAT YOU'RE
EATING.
>> OH, WHAT!
>> Jeff: THESE ARE SHIP WORMS.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> ARE THEY ALIVE?
>> Jeff: THEY'RE NOT ACTUALLY
WORMS.
THEY'RE PART CLAM FAMILY.
THINK OF THESE AS THE OCEAN'S
EQUIVALENT OF A TERMITE.
THEY'LL BORE THROUGH SHIPS,
THEY'LL EAT WOOD.
>> AND THEY HAVE BONES.
>> YOU WORMS.
>> I LIKE THE FACT THAT THIS IS
SLIMY.
IT JUST WETS MY APPETITE.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
THREE ARE MOVING ON.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> DO IT, DO IT, DO IT!
>> COCHRAN!
>> Jeff: GOTTA GET IT ALL THE
WAY DOWN.
>> TAKE IT DOWN, GUYS.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM IS THERE,
EDDIE IS THERE.
ONE SPOT LEFT.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: COCHRAN MOVING ON.
WOW, THAT WAS FAST.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> ANDREA, GREAT JOB.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE A SHIP WORM
MUSTACHE, ANDREA.
ANDREA, PHILLIP AND MICHAEL TAKE
A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE, EDDIE,
COCHRAN AND MALCOLM.
NEXT ROUND.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: TWO WILL MOVE INTO
THE FINAL ROUND.
ONE OF YOU WILL JOIN THE OTHER
LOSERS ON THE BENCH.
REVEAL.
>> YOU CAN DO THIS, GUYS.
>> THESE ARE DUCK EMBRYOS.
>> WHY?
WHY?
>> GO GET THEM, GUYS.
>> I CAN SEE THE FEATHERS.
>> Jeff: GO AHEAD AND SEPARATE
THE SHELL.
SET IT BACK DOWN.
( LAUGHTER ).
YOU CAN SEE THE FECTERS.
>> ETY, THERE'S NOTHING.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN SEE LAILGT
BEAK.
THIS IS A DELICACY WE USED
BEFORE BUT IT ORIGINATED HERE IN
THE PHILIPPINES.
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
>> MINE'S STILL MOVING.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO, TWO MOVE ON TO THE FINAL
ROUND.
>> COME OGUYS!
>> Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> EDDIE, COME ON, COME ON!
>> Jeff: COCHRAN!
HE'S MOVING ON.
IT IS BETWEEN EDDIE AND MALCOLM
TO JOIN COCHRAN IN THE FINAL.
EDDIE, WHO SPITS SOME UP, BUT
HE'S GOT TO FIND THAT TO GET IT
BACK DOWN.
MALCOLM STILL CHEWING.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> LET'S GO!
MALCOLM, YOU GOT IT!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM MOVING ON
VERSUS COCHRAN IN THE FINAL
ROUND!
( APPLAUSE )
>> I LOVE THAT COCHRAN NAILED
IT.
>> Jeff: EDDIE COULD NOT KEEP
IT DOWN.
>> I BIT THE BEAK.
THAT WAS THE FIRST THING BIT.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, MALCOLM,
TAKES YOUR SPOTS AT THE FINAL
MEAL.
COCHRAN, IN THE FINALS OF AN
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> MALCOLM!
>> LET'S GO, COCHRAN!
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Jeff: THIS IS DAVID AND
GOLIATH.
I MEAN, EATING.
>> HE SAID GINGER KOBASHI.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO AGAINST
THAT?
>> BRING IT ON.
>> Jeff: LET'S REVEAL THE
FINAL FOOD ITEM.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE BRAINS.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE RIGHT.
IT IS PIG BRAINS.
>> IT'S BACON!
( LAUGHTER )
>> BACK OF YOUR THROAT.
SWALLOW IT WHOLE.
>> Jeff: THE FIRST PERSON TO
SHOW ME A COMPLETELY EMPTY
MOUTH, WINS IMMUNITY, IT SAFE AT
THE VOTE, GUARANTEED A ONE IN 11
SHOT OF WINNING THIS GAME.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> Jeff:S THIS GOING TO GO
FAST.
COCHRAN PULLS IT OUT FOR
IMMUNITY!
( APPLAUSE )
>> COCHRAN!
YEAH!
>> Jeff: TAKE IT IN, BROTHER.
>> WOW.
>> GOOD JOB, MALCOLM.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, COME ON
OVER.
>> I'VE BEEN WAITING MY WHOLE
LIFE FOR THIS.
IT'S GOING TO TOUCH MY
SHOULDERS.
IT'S GOING TO BE INCREDIBLE.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: COCHRAN!
SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 22
DAYS, SOMEBODY WILL BE GOING
HOME TONIGHT.
GET YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANKS.
>> GOOD JOB, COCHRAN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> PUBLISHED MY EXCESSIVE
CELEBRATION.
IT'S JUST I'M VERY AWARE THERE
ARE VERY FEW CHALLENGES I HAVE A
CHANCE OF WINNING.
>> THIS IS SO BAD-ASS, TOO.
IT REALLY IS.
>> I THINK IT WAS TAILOR MADE
FOR ME.
TODAY A IMMUNITY CHALLENGE WAS A
TRUE "SURVIVOR" CLASSIC AND THE
FACT I GOT TO THE FIND ROUND AND
THE FINAL ROUND WAS BETWEEN ME,
THIS LITTLE PIP-SQUEAK, AND
MALCOLM, THE GOLDEN GOD OF THIS
TRIBE.
AND THE FACT THAT I WON IS DREAM
FULFILLMENT.
>> YOU'RE A TRUE SURVIVOR.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> WE'RE LEADERSHIP FOR YOU.
THIS OVER-THE-TOP, SOMEWHAT
OBNOXIOUS VICTORY CELEBRATION
BECAUSE I KNOW THIS MOMENT
PROBABLY ISN'T GOING TO HAPPEN
AGAIN.
ANY OTHER INDIVIDUAL HAVING THAT
SORT OF DISPLAY OF BASICALLY BAD
SPORTSMANSHIP IT WOULD HAVE
RUBBED THEM THE WRONG WAY BUT
SOMEHOW EVERYBODY SEEMED HAPPY
FOR ME.
AND NOW I FINALLY KNOW THE
THRILL OF VICTORY.
>> COCHRAN, OF ALL PEOPLE, WON
IMMUNITY TODAY.
I'M HAPPY FOR HIM.
YOU KNOW.
I LIKE COCHRAN BUT SINCE I DONT
PLAN ON KEEPING HIM AROUND THAT
LONG I'M GLAD WE GOT THIS DONE
EARLY SO HE CAN CHECK THAT OFF
THE BUCKET LIST.
>> NO ONE WANTS US AROUND.
>> EVERYONE WANTS TO THROW US
UNDER THE BUS.
>> SO IT MAKES SENSE TO STICK
TOGETHER.
>> I TALKED TO CORINNE, SHE'S
TOTALLY ON BOARD.
>> REYNOLD IS DOWN.
>> CORINNE BRING ALONG MIKE.
>> YEAH.
>> PHILLIP'S DEFINITELY GONNA BE
GUNNING FOR ME OR REYNOLD.
>> THIS IS THE ONLY STRESSFUL
ONE BECAUSE THE NUMBERS ARE
TIGHT.
>> THEY'RE HUGE.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE GOT ALL MY
TROOPS IN LINE BBUT THE
SITUATION IS VERY FLUID AND THE
ONLY CERTAINTY IS WE ARE GOING
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THERE ARE A LOT OF INDEPENDENT,
FREE THINKERS AROUND HERE.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO FALL
INTO LINE IF THIS THING IS GOING
TO WORK.
LUCKILY, CORINNE IS IN MY
CORNER, AND SHE'S DEFINITELY A
FIGHTER.
SO WHAT I'M THINKING IS WE DO
A SPLIT VOTE.
BETWEEN EDDIE AND REYNOLD.
THEREBY SENDING ONE OF THE TWO
POWER BASES HOME.
THAT'S THE MOST PRUDENT THING TO
DO.
>> YEAH, WELL, I'M NOT A BIG FAN
OF THE SPLIT VOTE.
>> JUST THINK ABOUT.
>> LET ME PITCH SOMETHING ELSE
TO YOU.
EDDIE AND REYNOLD AND ALL THE
FANS WANT SHERRI GONE.
THEY DON'T LIKE SHERRI.
WHY DON'T WE JUST TAKE SHERRI
OUT FIRST AND MAKE IT AN EASY
FIRST VOTE AND SPLIT THE SECOND
VOTE.
>> THE PROBLEM FOR THAT FOR ME
IS I WANT A BIG FISH TO GO HOME
THE FIRST TIME.
>> I EXPECTED THIS WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
PHILLIP IS TALKIN TALKING ABOUT
SPLITTING VOTES AND FLUSHING
THE
IDOL OUT BECAUSE I WANT TO AVOID
THAT AT ALL COST.
I NEED REYNOLD AND EDDIE.
AND I DON'T WANT THEM FLIPPING
OUT.
>> I BELIEVE IN GETTING RID OF
OF THE POWER FIRST.
>> I WAS FURIOUS THAT HE
WOULDN'T EVEN LISTEN TO WHAT I
HAD TO SAY AND JUST HIS UTTER
DISREGARD FOR ANYONE ELSE'S
FEELINGS.
AND THAT WAS IT.
I WASN'T ALREADY GOING TO TURN,
THAT SEALED MY FATE.
>> LOOK, MY ONLY CONCERN,
REALLY, IS I DON'T WANT SPLIT
VOTES.
IF YOU WANT TO TAKE OUT
LITERALLY ANYBODY I'LL TAKE THEM
OUT.
I FEEL LIKE SHERRI IS AN EASY
ONE.
>> PHILLIP WILL BE THE HARDEST
TO CONVINCE.
>> BUT HE'S ONE PERSON.
WE DON'T NEED HIM.
WE SHOULD STRONG ARM HIM LIKE HE
STRONG ARMS US.
THAT'S WHAT HE DOES TO ME ALL
THE TIME.
>> CORIN ADAMANT WE DON'T
TARGET EDDIE AND REYNOLD.
IF SHERRI GOES, NO SWEAT OFF MY
BACK.
SHERRI IS AN EASY VOTE AND HER
ELIMINATION WOULD LOCK THE
FAVORITES' NUMBERS IN A WAY THAT
WOULD BE IRREVERSIBLE.
>> I THINK AT THIS POINT WE NEED
TO MAKE A STATEMENT TO HIM.
>> IF HE'S COMPLETELY
OUTNUMBERED, HE'S NOT GOING TO
BE A VOCAL MINORITY ABOUT IT.
WHAT DOESN'T BODY WELL IS CORAND
I KNOW PHILLIP HATE EACHING AND
HAVE A SUSPICION OF EACH OTHER
THAT IS UNHEALTHY AND IF THE
FAVORITES DON'T COME TOGETHER,
THAT IS ADMITTING TO THE WORLD,
FANS INCLUDING, THAT WE'RE A
DYSFUNCTIONAL GROUP THAT DOESN'T
TRUST EACH OTHER, THERE ARE
OPENINGS, AND WE'RE APT TO FALL
APART, GIVEN THE RIGHT CATALYST.
>> AND DAWN IS ACTUALLY ON THE
OUTS.
SHE'S PROBABLY WILLING TO COME
WITH US, TOO.
WE HAVE TO GET THROUGH THE FIRST
VOTE.
>> WE HAVE TO KNOCK OUT SHERRI.
>> SURE.
>> HOPEFULLY THAT LAIB SLAM-DUNK
AND THEN WE CAN MOVE FROM THERE.
>> I'VE HITCHED MY WAGON TO THIS
MALCOLM AND CORINNE
COUNTER-ALLIANCE AND THEY'RE
RECEPTIVE TO THE IDEA OF
BRINGING SOME OF THE FANS IN AND
OVER-THROWING THE TYRANNY OF
LORD PHILLIP OF THE HIGH
SHELTER.
AND I'M JUST LIKE, THIS IS
AMAZING.
>> PHILLIP'S GOT THIS
GRANDIOSE-- HE THINKS HE IS
TOTALLY GOING TO THE END.
>> THE WAY HE WALKS AROUND CAMP,
TOO.
>> YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
>> IT'S SO POMPOUS.
>> I WANT TO PUNCH HIM EVERY
DAY.
I HATE HIM.
HATE.
AS LONG AS YOU TRUST ME, I'LL
TRUST YOU.
DON'T WAIVER.
LET'S CLEAN UP THE HOUSE.
>> LET'S CLEAN IT UP.
>> I'M GOING TO GO BACK.
>> OBVIOUSLY, EDDIE AND I HAVE
BEEN DELUSIONALLY OPTIMISTIC THE
ENTIRE GAME.
IF THIS VOTE GOES AS PLANNED, IS
IT & SHERRI GOING GZ HOME I'LL
DEFINITELY BE IN AN ALLIANCE
THAT'S CALLING THE SHOTS AND
I'LL BE BACK IN BUSINESS.
BUT WHAT
I'M LOOKING AT IS AM I BEING
HURT?
I DO FEEL LIKE THIS ALLIANCE IS
A DEMOCRACY?
DO I FEEL LIKE WHEN I COME WITH
A POINT, DO PEOPLE TREAT ME LIKE
I'M AN IDIOT.
>> AFTER THIS VOTE, IF PHILLIP
KEEPS TREATING ME THE WAY HE HAS
I WANT HIM GOING GUNN.
THE REASON IT'S EASY TO TAKE
PHILLIP IS YOU CAN GET ANYBODY
BEHIND IT.
MALCOLM WOULD DO IT.
EDDIE AND REYNOLD ARE VERY
WILLING TO PLAY BALL.
>> WHAT ABOUT MICHAEL?
>> 100% VOTE.
>> THAT'S, LIKE, SIX PEOPLE.
MALCOLM, YOU--
>> ERIK.
>> IF ERIK'S IN, TOO, THAT'S,
LIKE, SEVEN.
CORINNE IS SUGGESTING I JOIN
WITH THEM AND BREAK UP THE
ALLIANCE OF THE FAVORITES, AND
I'M THINKING, OKAY, HERE WE GO
AGAIN.
LAST TIME I PLAYED I CAME INTO
THIS KIND OF INFORMATION, AND I
DIDN'T SHARE IT WITH ANYBODY,
AND THAT WAS MY DOWNFALL LAST
TIME.
SO I CAN'T REPEAT THAT SAME
MISTAKE.
SHE WANTS TO BLINDSSIDE PHILLIP
AND THE REST OF THE FAVORITES
AND SHE'S GOT THE FANS TO DO IT.
THOSE GUYS ARE IN HER BACK
POCKET NOW.
>> DAWN JUST APPROACHED ME VERY
FRANTIC SAYING CORINNE LET IT BE
KNOWN THAT APPARENTLY SHE
REALLIED THIS GROUP OF TROOPS
TOGETHER THAT GIVES HER THE
NUMBERS AND POST-MERGE CONTROL
OF THE GAME.
>> AND WE'RE GOING TO TAKE OUT
SHERRI, SO WE'LL BE AT 11 AND
THEY'LL BE AT SIX.
WE SHOULD HAVE BEEN VOTING OUT
REYNOLD OR EDDIE, WHICH IS
CORINNE'S DOING.
>> YEAH.
OH, BROTHER.
>> I PROMISE IF I HAD NUMBERS TO
VOTE HER OUT TONIGHT, I WOULD
VOTE HER OUT.
>> WOULD LOVE THAT.
>> SHERRI'S A POSSIBLE VOTE WITH
US, SO...
>> I THINK WE HAVE BRENDA.
>> EVEN WE GOT BRENDA TONIGHT.
BRENDA, YOU, ME, ANDREA,
PHILLIP.
SHERRI IS STILL SIX.
THEN IT'S A TIE.
>> CORINNE, WHO I THOUGHT DIDN'T
HAVE A STRATEGIC BONE IN HER
BODY, SHE'S POSITIONED HERSELF
IN A WAY THAT WE HAVE BEEN
BASICALLY ACQUIESCING TO EVERY
DEMAND SHE'S MADE.
SO IT'S A SOBERING SITUATION,
AND IF WE DON'T COME UP WITH A
PLAN IT COULD BE DEVASTATING TO
MY GAME AND THE GAME OF MY
ALLIES.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> APPARENTLY, LIKE, CORINNE
APPROACHED DAWN AND SHE MADE IT
SOUND LIKE SHE HAS REYNOLD,
EDDIE, MALCOLM, ERIK, AND
MICHAEL.
AND IF WE VOTE OFF SHERRI
TONIGHT OORKTS FIVE VERSUS SIX.
AND THEY'LL VOTE OFF PHILLIP
NEXT.
>> YEAH.
>> IF WE'RE ON THE WRONG SIDE OF
THE NUMBERS, WE'RE DEAD.
>> HM.
EVERYONE WAS ON BOARD WITH
VOTING SHERRI OUT, AND THEN I
HEARD THAT COIRN IS TALKING
ABOUT POSSIBLY FLIPPING, AND IF
SHE CAN PULL ALL THESE PEOPLE,
THEN WE'RE ALL SCREWED.
SO SHE'S DANGEROUS.
>> CORINNE IS FREAKING CALLING
EVERY VOTE.
>> I'M KIND OF UP FOR A LITTLE
BLINDSIDE.
>> IT WOULD BE FANTASTIC IF YOU
THINK IT'S POSSIBLE TO DO.
>> WELL, IF WE CAN GET SHERRI
AND-- ERIK'S WISHY-WASHY.
I GUESS HE WOULD GO ALONG WITH
WHAT MALCOLM.
IT'S RIDICULOUS TO THINK I'M
COUNTING ON SHERRI, WHO IS ONE
OF THE FANS, AND EVEN ERIK, OF
ALL PEOPLE.
HE'S THE HUGE QUESTION MARK
BECAUSE HE DISTRIBUTE TALK
STRATEGY TO ANYBODY WHICH MAKES
ME NERVOUS BECAUSE I HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT HE'S THINKING.
>> CORINNE, SHE HAS REYNOLD,
EDDIE, AND MICHAEL.
SHE HAS ENOUGH PEOPLE TO
BLINDSIDE YOU NEXT VOTE AFTER
SHER EERK WHICH MEANS THEN IT'S
ME NEXT--
>> SHE'S NOT THINKING OF ANYBODY
BUT HERSELF.
I'VE BEEN SAYING THAT ALL ALONG.
>> WHY DON'T WE GET RID OF HER
TONIGHT?
>> I WANT TO DO THAT.
MY CORE ALLIANCE CAME THROUGH IN
A BIG WAY.
CORINNE, SHE'S RUNNING AROUND
TELLING EVERYBODY SHE'S GOT A
COALITION TO VOTE OUT WHO, THE
SPECIALIST, OUT OF THE GAME, ME,
PHILLIP SHEPPARD.
HOW DARE SHE TRY TO GET ME OUT
OF THE GAME?
I'M THE ONE WHO ORIGINALLY
BROUGHT HER IN, AND I WILL NOT
ALLOW CORINNE TO TAKE CONTROL OF
THIS GAME.
WELL, SUFFICE IT TO SAY FITELL
TO YOU VOTE CORINNE AND YOU DID
IT, YOU WOULD HAVE AUTOMATICALLY
CHANGED YOUR FATE BECAUSE THIS
WILL TELL ME IF I CAN USE YOU
AGAIN.
>> PHILLIP CAME UP TO ME AND
SAID, "IF YOU WANT TO GO FURTHER
IN THIS GAME, YOU NEED TO VOTE
OUT CORINNE AND COME WITH US.
I'M FIGHTING HARD TO STAY IN
THIS GAME, AND I'M WILLING TO
MAKE A REALLY BIG MOVE.
THE PROBLEM SI CAN'T STAND
PHILLIP.
HE'S SO ARROGANT.
>> JUST POINT TO THE NAME.
IT'S JUST NOT HANGING RIGHT.
OKAY.
>> IT'S DISCONCERTING THAT MY
FATE IN THIS GAME RIGHT NOW
RESTS IN THE HANDS OF SOMEBODY
LIKE SHERRI WHO IS DESPERATE FOR
SOME SORT OF FOOTING IN THE
GAME.
AND YOU HAVE ERIK THE ICE CREAM
SCOOPER, SOMEBODY WHO DISTRIBUTE
LIKE STRATEGY AND PROVED HIMSELF
TO BE INCOMPETENT WITH PLAYING
THIS GAME.
>> THIS THING'S HAPPENING LIKE
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS ALREADY.
SO WE'LL JUST VOTE FOR SHERRI.
>> MALCOLM CAME UP TO ME AND
SAID, "VOTE FOR SHERRI."
ANDREA SAID VOTE OUT CORINNE.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON
BUT I FEEL LIKE I'M SWING VOTE
SO I'M SUDDENLY BECOMING A VERY
VALUABLE PLAYER, WHICH IS SO
COOL.
I JUST WISH I KNEW WHAT I WAS
GOING TO DO.
>> Jeff: WOW.
12 PEOPLE LEFT.
SO SINCE THE SWITCH, ONLY FANS
HAVE BEEN VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
MICHAEL, DOES IT SEEM LIKE A
FAIR ASSUMPTION TO MAKE THAT
THAT WOULD CONTINUE TONIGHT?
>> I THINK IT IS A FAIR
ASSUMPTION.
IT'S BEEN PRETTY CLEAR TO US
THAT THE FAVORITES ARE GOING TO
BE STICKING TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: CORINNE AS SOMEBODY
WHO HAS PLAYED THIS GAME YOU CAN
APPRECIATE WHAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
TO BE IN THE POSITION OF THE
FANS WHERE IT FEELS A LITTLE
HELPLESS.
>> YEAH, IT'S BLEAK, BUT, YOU
KNOW, A SITUATION IS NEVER
HELPLESS.
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT ABOUT--
IF YOU COME DO ME WITH A GOOD
IDEA, I'LL PROBABLY LISTEN.
>> Jeff: DAWN, CORINNE IS
SAYING, LISTEN, I'M OPEN.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE EIGHT
FAVORITES, FOUR FANS.
>> WELL, THERE'S 12 OF US, AND
12 OF US AREN'T GOING TO BE IN
THE FINAL THREE SO IT MAKES
SENSE THAT WE'RE ALL TRYING TO
MAKE DECISIONS THAT WILL FURTHER
US IN THE GAME LONGER TERM.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, DOES IT
CONCERN YOU THAT CORINNE WOULD
BE HONEST ENOUGH TO SAY, "TALK
TO ME."
THAT'S OPENING A DOOR.
>> THAT'S ONE OF THE GOOD THINGS
ABOUT CORINNE, SHE IS SO OPEN
AND HONEST ABOUT IT.
I WOULD BE A LITTLE MORE WORRIED
IF SHE DIDN'T SAY SHE WAS OPEN
TO THAT POSSIBILITY.
THAT WOULD MAKE ME MORE
SUSPICIOUS.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, WHAT DO YOU
DO?
YOU'VE SEEN FAN GONE, FAN GONE,
FAN GONE, AND YOU'RE UP AGAINST
EIGHT PEOPLE WHO KNOW HOW TO
PLAY THIS GAME.
>> IF YOU'RE A FAVORITE AND
PLAYED THIS GAME BEFORE YOU KNOW
IF YOU'RE NOT ON THE TOP THREE
OR FOUR OF THIS POWERHOUSE
ALLIANCE, NOW IS THE TIME TO
START MAKING SOME MOVES.
YOU HAVE FOUR MORE CHESS PIECES
TO PLAY WITH HERE, SO I'M NOT
COUNT, THE FANS OUT YET.
>> Jeff: ERIK, REYNOLD MAKES A
GOOD ARGUMENT.
NOT EVERYBODY CAN BE IN THE TOP
THREE IN AN ALLIANCE OF EIGHT.
>> RIGHT.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST THE WAY THE
GAME GOES.
THERE'S ALWAYS GOING TO BE
SOMEBODY ON THE BOTTOM WHO IS
DESPERATE TO GET BACK INTO
SOMETHING ELSE.
SO THAT'S PRETTY MUCH OF THE
DYNAMIC I FEEL LIKE IS GOING ON
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, IT'S GOOD
NEWS/BAD NEWS BEING A RETURNING
PLAYER.
THE GOOD NEWS IS YOU PLAYED
BEFORE.
THE BAD NEWS IS, YOU PLAYED
BEFORE SO YOU KNOW AT SOME POINT
SOMEBODY IS NOT GOING TO TELL
YOU THE TRUTH AND IT MIGHT BE
TONIGHT.
>> I AM SO MUCH MORE PARANOID
THIS TIME AROUND BECAUSE I KNOW
A LOT OF THESE PEOPLE ARE REALLY
GOOD AT DECEIVING AND REALLY
GOOD AT LYING.
>> Jeff: CORINNE, WOULD YOU
AGREE WITH THAT?
>> I WILL GIVE YOU A QUOTE, MICE
TYSON SAYS EVERYBODY HAS A PLAN
UNTIL YOU GET PUNCHED IN THE
FACE.
EVERYBODY ELSE, EVEN THE
FAVORITES, AS COMFORTABLE AS WE
MAY SEEM, EVERY ONE OF US IS
WAITING TO GET PUNCHED IN THE
FACE.
>> Jeff: SHERRI, IS THERE
ANYTHING YOU CAN DO IF YOU'RE A
FAN AT THIS POINT?
>> I THINK THE FANS DON'T HAVE A
SHOT.
>> Jeff: DO YOU BELIEVE THAT?
>> I DO.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, TOUGH SPOT
TO BE IN IF YOU'RE A FAN RIGHT
NOW.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE THERE'S
ANYBODY UP HERE YOU CAN LOOK AT
AND SAY THEY'RE AN EASY MARK.
>> RIGHT.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: WOULD YOU AGREE?
>> I THINK THERE'S A LOT MORE
MANEUVERING THAT'S GOING ON THAN
IS EVEN COMING OUT IN THIS
TRIBAL COUNCIL RIGHT NOW.
IT HASN'T ALL BUBBLED TO THE
SURFACE YET, BUT THIS BUBBLE IS
ABOUT TO POP PRETTY SOON.
MAYBE NOT TONIGHT, BUT THERE'S A
LOT GOING ON.
>> Jeff: YOU DON'T THINK
TONIGHT'S VOTE IS GOING TO BE A
BIG SHOCKER.
>> I'M NOT NECESSARILY SURE
TONIGHT'S VOTE IS GOING TO BE A
BIG SHOCKER, BUT I THINK THERE
ARE SOME SHOCKERS ON THE WAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WITH THAT,
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
PHILLIP, YOU'RE UP.
>> CORINNE, YOU ARE ONE OF THE
MOST SELFISH PEOPLE I HAVE EVER
MET IN MY LIFE.
>> YOU PLAYED A GOOD GAME BUT,
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU, I WASN'T
LOOKING FOR APPLICATIONS FOR NEW
FRIENDS.
>> YOU'RE DANGEROUS.
I JUST HOPE THAT EVERYBODY DOES
WHAT THEY SAID THEY WERE GOING
TO DO.
I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
>> HEY, LADY, I'M SORRY TO WRITE
YOUR NAME DOWN.
I'M JUST TRYING TO STAY ALIVE
ANOTHER DAY, AND I HOPE YOU'RE
NOT TOO UPSET.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY TNO OF NOW WOULD BE THE
TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SHERRI.
SHERRI.
THREE VOTES SHERRI.
FIVE VOTES SHERRI.
CORINNE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CORINNE.
FOUR VOTES CORINNE.
WE'RE TIED, 5 VOTES SHERRI, FIVE
VOTES CORINNE, TWO VOTES LEFT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
CORINNE.
SIX VOTES CORINNE, FIVE VOTES
SHERRI, ONE VOTE LEFT.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES," CORINNE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
CORINNE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, JUDGING FROM THE LOOK ON
CORINNE'S FACE, THAT WAS
ANYTHING BUT A STRAIGHTFORWARD
VOTE.
AND I'M GUESSING IT WON'T BE THE
LAST TIME WE ARE SURPRISED AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": IT'S TIME FOR
MALCOLM TO MAKE A MOVE.
>> IF WE'RE GONNA DO SOMETHING,
IT HAS TO BE NOW.
>> THEY THOUGHT THEY CUT OFF THE
HEAD OF THE SNAKE.
>> Jeff: AND EDDIE FLIRTS HIS
WAY BACK INTO THE GAME.
>> I AM INDIRECTLY HITTING ON
YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO GOES OUT
HERE AND ACTUALLY FALLS FOR
SOMEONE.
I MEAN, IT'S REALLY RARE.
>> IN CABONE, THE PEOPLE I
PLAYED WITH WERE CLOSE TO MY
HEART, HERE, I DIDN'T LIKE
ANYBODY OTHER THAN MICHAEL AND
MALCOLM.
I KNEW THERE WERE PROBLEMS,
WHICH IS WHY I WAS LOOKING TO
MOVE OUT TO A DIFFERENT
ALLIANCE.
UNFORTUNATELY, I'M OUT OF THE
GAME.
YOU JUST GOTTA LOOK AT IT AS I
GOT TO SPEND 22 DAYS IN AN
AWESOME PARADISE AND I MADE SOME
NEW MEMORIES.