>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
AFTER THE MERGE, MALCOLM,
REYNOLD, AND EDDIE FOUND
THEMSELVES ON THE OUTSIDE OF
STEALTH "R" US,AN UNBREAKABLE
ALLIANCE OF SEVEN LED BY
PHILLIP.
BUT THEY WERE GAINING CONFIDENCE
AND WERE READY TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE.
>> I STILL HAVE AN IDOL.
I'M NOT GOING DOWN WITHOUT SOME
FIREWORKS.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, THE LEADER
OF STEALTH "R" US, WAS ALSO
CONFIDENT.
>> I FEEL LIKE I JUST MIGHT HAVE
A SHOT OF WINNING.
>> Jeff: HE HAD A STRONG
ALLIANCE AND BELIEVED NOTHING
COULD GET IN THEIR WAY.
>> ONE OF THE BEAUTIES OF BEING
THE NUMBERS 7-3 IS THAT IT
DOESN'T MATTER.
ONE OF THOSE THREE ARE GOING TO
GO HOME.
>> STEALTH!
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, REYNOLD FOUND THE
STRENGTH TO WIN.
REYNOLD WINS IMMUNITY!
>> Jeff: AND BACK AT CAMP
MALCOLM FOUND ANOTHER HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> MALCOLM JUST FOUND THE IDOL.
>> WHO CARES?
WE GOT THE NUMBERS, BABE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
STEALTH "R" US THOUGHT THEY HAD
AN EASY VOTE.
>> EVERYONE'S LOOKING AT EDDIE
BECAUSE MALCOLM HAPPENED UPON
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> Jeff: BUT IT QUICKLY TURNED
INTO ONE OF THE CRAZIEST TRIBAL
COUNCIL IT IS GAME HAS EVER
SEEN.
>> THIS IS THE OTHER IMMUNITY
IDOL I'VE BEEN HANGING ON TO.
I'M GIVING IT TO EDDIE.
I HAD THAT ONE FOR A WHILE.
I JUST FOUND THE OTHER ONE
TODAY.
ONE OF THE SEVEN OF THIS VERY
TIGHT GROUP ARE GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: WITH THE THREE AMIGOS
NOW IN CONTROL, THEY TRIED TO
CONVINCE PHILIP'S ALLIANCE TO
TURN ON HIM.
>> WE'LL JUST THROW IT OUT
THERE.
THE THREE OF US ARE VOTING FOR
PHILLIP.
PHILLIP IS THE FUN SPONGE, HE
SUCKS IT OUT OF THE GROUP.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, THE ONLY
MEMBER OF THE STEALTH "R" US
ALLIANCE TO CHANGE THEIR VOTE
WAS ERIC, BUT IT WAS ENOUGH.
PHILLIP, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: LEAVING STEALTH "R"
US WITHOUT ITS LEADER.
NINE ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
>> IT'S NICE TO BE ABLE TO SAY
HI AND TALK TO YOU GUYS.
>> WOW, YEAH.
>> GOING INTO IT I WAS LIKE THIS
MIGHT NOT WORK OUT.
>> YOU GUYS THOUGHT WE WERE
TRYING TO PULL ONE OVER ON YOU.
WE WERE JUST LIKE IT IS WORTH
THREE IMMUNITIES TO US.
>> I REALLY THOUGHT YOU WERE
GENUINE.
>> WITH THE EXECUTION OF THE
SPECIALIST PHILLIP SHEPHERD, I
THINK STEALTH "R" US HOPEFULLY
IS GOING TO FRACTURE.
>> NOW I NEVER HAVE TO USE THE
PHRASE STEALTH "R" US EVER
AGAIN.
>> THANK GOODNESS!
(LAUGHTER)
>> IF THOSE SIX PEOPLE STICK
TOGETHER, I DON'T HAVE A CHANCE
IN THIS GAME.
IF I KNOCK OFF THEIR LEADER,
MAYBE ONE TWO WILL FRACTURE AND
COME TO THE DARK SIDE WITH ME
AND THE THREE AMIGOS.
>> THERE'S NOT REALLY ANYTHING I
DISLIKE ABOUT PHILLIP IN THIS
GAME EXCEPT FOR THE FACT THAT HE
CAN'T FIT HIS HEAD AND EGO
UNDERNEATH THE SHELTER.
THE STABILITY HAS BEEN ROCKED
OUT OF THE GAME.
LIKE, THE LEGS HAVE BEEN KICKED
OUT UNDER THE CHAIR OF STEALTH
"R" US AND IT OPENS ME UP TO
TALKING WITH PEOPLE THAT PHILLIP
DIDN'T WANT KNOW TALK TO.
>> HE WAS HIS OWN DOWNFALL.
>> I KNOW.
>> THE TRICK KEY PART NOW IS
DECIDING WHEN TO VOTE WITH THE
THREE BOYS AND WHEN TO VOTE WITH
THE REMAINING FAVORITES.
AND I ENJOY THAT POSITION
BECAUSE I CAN CHOOSE AT THE LAST
MINUTE WHICH OPTION IS BETTER
FOR ERIC.
>> I FEEL BEAT.
>> I FEEL WHOOPED.
I'VE NEVER BEEN THIS TIRED
BEFORE.
DAY 29.
>> I'VE PARTICIPATED IN AND
CERTAINLY VIEWED HUNDREDS OF
TRIBAL COUNCILS.
NEVER BEFORE HAVE I SEEN
ANYTHING QUITE LIKE WHAT
HAPPENED LAST NIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IT LEFT ME BREATHLESS, IT LEFT
ME TERRIFIED.
TODAY'S BEEN A PRETTY ROUGH DAY
AROUND CAMP.
PEOPLE ARE REALLY HUNGRY AND
SPIRITS HAVE BEEN LOW AND IT WAS
DRIVING EVERYBODY CRAZY.
THERE AREN'T TOO MANY DAYS OF
THIS LEFT, OR DAYS LIKE THIS.
>> YOU OKAY?
YOU WANT SOME WATER?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
THE BRANDON DAYS, THE SWAPS, THE
MERGE, THE VOTING PEOPLE OUT.
>> HUGE SURPRISES LIKE LAST
NIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
STUFF LIKE THAT SCARES ME
BECAUSE FOR THE THREE GUYS TO
STAY AND THEN FOR US SEVEN TO
LOOK AT EACH OTHER AND BE LIKE
ONE OF US IS GOING HOME IT -- IT
THREW A BIG THING IN MY PLAN.
SO LOSING CONTROL OF THE GAME,
IT'S TERRIFYING.
IT'S JUST WHEN YOUR BODY IS LIKE
--
>> I KNOW.
YOU'VE LOST A LOT OF WEIGHT,
TOO.
KEEP DRINKING.
WE'VE GOT TO GET EVERYBODY
DRINKING.
>> REALLY, HOW CAN WE LIVE OFF
OF WATER.
>> YOU CAN.
>> IT'S SO DEPRESSING, YOU KNOW?
IT'S JUST A LITTLE HARD WITH THE
EMOTIONS, THE FOOD SITUATION,
THE LOW ENERGY AND WITH THAT
UNCERTAINTY OF WHAT THESE BOYS
ARE CAPABLE OF.
>> GUYS, WE GOT SOME TREEMAIL.
>> I KNEW IT!
I KNEW IT!
>> YAY!
COME ON!
>> WHAT DO WE HAVE?
(ULULATING)
>> 500 BUCKS IN CASH!
>> OH, MY GOD!
WE SAW THERE WERE
NINE ENVELOPES SITTING THERE
AND I KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS AS A
"SURVIVOR" FAN.
IT MEANS THE FOOD OPTION IS UPON
US YUP, 500 BUCKS IN CASH.
DO YOU REALLY NEED A LITTLE
POEM?
>> NEGATIVE!
WE'RE GOOD.
>> WE'RE GOING TO AN AUCTION.
HALLELUJAH, IT COULD HAVEN'T
COME AT A BETTER TIME BECAUSE
THERE IS A CHANCE THAT THERE'S
GOING TO BE SOME SORT OF BIG
ADVANTAGE IN THE GAME OFFERED UP
AND, CONSIDERING MY POSITION, I
DEFINITELY IS TO CONSIDER NOT
SPENDING ANY MONEY ON FOOD
TODAY.
I HATE THE THOUGHT OF IT, BUT
CONSIDERING WHERE I'M SITTING
RIGHT NOW I NEED ALL THE HELP I
CAN GET.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
I SEE SMILES ALREADY.
>> (LAUGHS).
>> Jeff: WHO DOESN'T LOVE THE
"SURVIVOR" AUCTION?
>> MY MONEY!
>> Jeff: THIS MORNING IN
TREEMAIL YOU WERE EACH GIVEN
$500 FOR THE "SURVIVOR" AUCTION.
BIDDING WILL BE IN $20
INCREMENTS.
NO SHARING OF MONEY.
NO SHARING OF FOOD.
THE AUCTION WILL END WITHOUT
WARNING SO DON'T MESS AROUND.
SHALL WE GET TO THE FIRST ITEM?
>> YES.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FIRST $20 GETS IT.
>> 20!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM!
>> THAT HAPPENED SO FAST.
>> I'VE LITERALLY BEEN PREPPING
MYSELF FOR HOURS, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO EAT.
I MIGHT HAVE JUST SHOT MYSELF IN
THE FOOT FOR THIS GAME FOR A
BEER AND SOME NUTS.
>> Jeff: IN ADDITION, TWO MORE
BEERS, PRETZELS TO GO WITH IT.
GIVE IT A TRY.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO IT RIGHT
THERE!
>> GOOD WORK!
>> WOW!
OH, MY GOSH!
YOUR EYES ARE RED ALREADY.
>> I KNOW!
>> Jeff: NEXT ITEM WILL REMAIN
COVERED.
>> $20.
>> $40.
>> $100.
>> Jeff: $100 TO DAWN.
>> Jeff: 140.
>> $160.
>> Jeff: $160 FOR A BLIND
ITEM.
>> $180.
>> Jeff: $180 TO REYNOLD.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
SOLD TO REYNOLD.
DON'T GET UP.
IF YOU WANT, WHAT YOU JUST
BOUGHT FOR $180 YOU CAN TRADE
FOR THIS.
OR --
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: YOU CAN TRADE IT FOR
THIS.
IT'S A MONTY HALL THING.
YOU'RE ALWAYS SUPPOSED TO
SWITCH.
>> Jeff: I DON'T TRUST YOU,
COCHRAN.
>> Jeff: THREE CHOICES.
>> MY GUT IS TELLING ME TO STICK
WITH THE INITIAL ONE.
>> Jeff: YOU BOUGHT THIS ITEM?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: COME ON UP.
>> Jeff: YOU WANT THE GOOD
NEWS OR THE BAD NEWS?
>> THE GOOD NEWS.
>> Jeff: THE GOOD NEWS IS YOU
DID NOT BUY A ROTTEN COCONUT.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHAT YOU
BOUGHT.
ONE SLICE OF PIZZA FOR $180.
THIS IS WHAT YOU GAVE UP.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: THE REST OF THE
PIZZA.
>> $500 FOR THE FULL PIZZA.
>> Jeff: SOLD TO SHERRY.
$500 FOR THE REST OF THE PIZZA.
TAKE A LITTLE PIECE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: SO, SHERRI, YOU
DIDN'T EVEN THINK THAT THERE
MIGHT BE SOMETHING ELSE DOWN THE
ROAD?
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, $500.
YOU'RE OUT OF THE AUCTION.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> Jeff: GO ENJOY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: WAY TO GO, SHERRI.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW WHAT THIS ONE
IS.
>> $500!
>> Jeff: WOW!
>> WAY TO GO, DAWN.
>> Jeff: SOLD TO DAWN, ROASTED
CHICKEN, $500.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: TAKE A BITE.
SHE DOESN'T EVEN WANT THE
UTENSILS.
>> I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE A BAT.
CAN I JUST SMELL IT?
OH, YEAH!
>> Jeff: NEXT ITEM.
THIS IS INFORMATION IN THIS
GAME.
$480.
>> Jeff: $480 TO MALCOLM.
IT WILL TAKE $500 TO GET IT.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE, SOLD TO
MALCOLM $480.
THAT IS THE REST OF THE MONEY
YOU HAVE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE 60 SECONDS
TO LOOK AT THIS.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: IN PRIVATE RIGHT
HERE.
>> I GOT 60 SECONDS TO READ AN
IDOL CLUE.
IT WAS PRETTY MUCH DIRECTIONS TO
WHERE THERE'S A BURIED HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
THERE'S NO WAY WITHOUT THIS CLUE
THIS IDOL IS GOING TO BE FOUND.
IT'S GOT TO BE SOMEWHERE TOWARDS
THE WELL AND I NEED ALL THE HELP
I CAN GET.
>> Jeff: THAT'S IT.
$480 FOR INFORMATION IN THE
GAME.
I HOPE IT WAS WORTH IT.
NEXT ITEM WILL REMAIN COVERED.
>> $100.
>> Jeff: BRENDA JUST JUMPS
RIGHT TO A HUNDRED.
>> Jeff: $200.
>> Jeff: ANDREA $200 WHICH
ANNOYS BRENDA.
>> IT'S JUST THAT I DON'T WANT
TO TAKE THE RISK AND I DON'T
WANT TO LOSE MONEY IF SOMEONE
ELSE HAS MORE MONEY AND THEN I
GET, LIKE, STUCK WITH SOMETHING
BAD.
>> Jeff: IT'S TOUGH OUT HERE.
THERE IS NO CERTAINTY IN THIS
GAME.
$260.
>> $280.
>> Jeff: ANDREA HAS IT AT
$280.
GOING ONCE.
GOING TWICE, SOLD.
ANDREA.
>> UH-OH.
>> Jeff: $280 FOR THIS.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> YAY!
>> SHE GOT WINE!
>> WOW, GOOD FOR YOU.
>> Jeff: AND YOU HAVE A
DILEMMA.
>> OH, NO.
>> Jeff: IT IS A BEAUTIFUL
MEAL CLEARLY WORTH $280.
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO GIVE THIS
UP, YOU CAN TAKE BACK FOR THE
TRIBE RICE AND BEANS.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: AND NOW THE DILEMMA
IS THERE'S A GROUP OF PEOPLE
BACK THERE STARVING BACK AT
CAMP.
>> OH, ANDREA --
>> I'LL TAKE THIS.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GIVING IT UP
FOR THE TRIBE?
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THANK YOU, ANDREA.
>> ANDREA, YOU'RE A SAINT!
>> OH, MY GOD, THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: NEXT ITEM, THIS IS AN
ADVANTAGE IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
>> OH!
>> $300.
>> Jeff: $300 TO REYNOLD.
>> $320.
>> Jeff: $320 TO BRENDA.
>> $340.
>> Jeff: $340 TO COCHRAN.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
SOLD TO COCHRAN.
COME ON UP!
THIS NOTE IS SEALED.
KEEP IT SEALED UNTIL THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> OKAY, WILL DO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GOOD LUCK.
>> ATTA BOY, COCHRAN.
>> Jeff: NEXT ITEM WILL REMAIN
COVERED.
>> $300.
>> OH, OKAY, GO.
>> Jeff: BRENDA JUMPS TO $300
OUT OF THE GATE.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE SOLD TO
BRENDA FOR $300.
YOUR WHOLE DILEMMA IN THIS
CHALLENGE HAS BEEN WHETHER OR
NOT I TAKE A RISK.
$300 BOUGHT YOU PIG BRAIN.
>> OKAY.
IRONICALLY, I DON'T FEEL LIKE
CRYING RIGHT NOW, WHICH IS
WEIRD.
>> Jeff: DO YOU WANT TO TRY
IT?
>> I JUST REMEMBERED THAT I
DON'T EAT PORK.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE EATING THE
BRAIN OF A PIG.
>> IT'S GOOD FOR YOU, RIGHT?
>> Jeff: I HAVE NO IDEA.
THIS IS AN EASY ONE.
I HAVE LETTERS FROM YOUR LOVED
ONES.
THEY WILL BE SOLD TO ANYBODY WHO
WANTS IT FOR $20.
>> $20!
>> NO MONEY, NO LOVED ONE
LETTERS FOR MALCOLM, SHERRI OR
DAWN.
>> I JUST PAID $500 FOR A
CHICKEN AND I COULD HAVE HAD
LETTERS FOR $20.
THAT'S CRAZY.
>> Jeff: DAWN, YOU'RE ALREADY
IN TEARS.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD.
I'LL TALK TO THEM IN TEN DAYS.
(SOBS)
>> I'M NOT CRYING BUT I FEEL THE
WAY THEY FEEL RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: HAND THEM OUT, THANK
YOU.
YOU GUYS CAN TAKE THESE BACK TO
CAMP AND READ THEM ONCE YOU GET
THERE.
THIS ITEM WILL REMAIN COVERED
AND IT COMES WITH A TWIST.
>> $180.
THAT'S ALL I GOT.
>> Jeff: $180 0-TO BRENDA.
>> $200.
>> Jeff: EDDIE PUT AN END TO
BRENDA'S DREAM WITH A BID OF
$200.
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE.
SOLD TO EDDIE, COME ON UP.
HERE'S THE TWIST: THE ITEM EDDIE
JUST BOUGHT IS TO BE SHARED BY
THE ENTIRE TRIBE.
>> WOW!
IT'S A GIANT JAR OF PEANUT
BUTTER.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: JUST GIVE IT A TRY.
>> HOW DID YOU GET THAT IN
THERE?
>> UNBELIEVABLE!
>> Jeff: YOU WILL HAVE 60
SECONDS TO SHARE THIS WITH
EVERYBODY.
ANYTHING ON YOUR FACE, YOUR
HANDS CAN GO BACK WITH YOU,
ANYTHING LEFT IN THE BOWL STAYS.
>> GET THE WATER OUT, BOYS, IT'S
STICKY.
>> Jeff: TIME STARTS NOW.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I'LL SCOOP UP STUFF AT THE
END.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, HOW OFTEN
DOES THAT HAPPEN?
>> MORE OFTEN THAN YOU THINK.
>> Jeff: AND THE "SURVIVOR"
AUCTION IS OVER.
>> Jeff: .
>> MALCOLM BOUGHT A CLUE WHICH
WAS MOST LIKELY FOR WHERE THE
LOCATION OF THE IDOL IS AND
PEOPLE ARE PSYCHED OUT BY LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL EVEN THOUGH
THERE'S ONLY THREE OF THEM,
MAYBE THEY'RE GOING TO PULL SOME
CRAZY THING.
AND BECAUSE THEY'VE GOT THAT
ARROGANCE THEY CAN GIVE A SENSE
OF NO MATTER WHAT THEY DO WE'LL
OUTPLAY THEM.
WE'LL OUTWIT THEM.
SO GO WITH US.
>> WE CAN EAT THREE TIMES A DAY.
>> OUR QUALITY OF LIFE JUST
CHANGED 1,000%.
AFTER THE AUCTION WE WENT FROM
BEING ABSOLUTELY MOROSE TO NOW,
LIKE, EVERYONE'S WELL FED.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF PROVISIONS TO
GET THROUGH THE REST OF THE GAME
AND MY ALLIANCE HAS AN IDOL
CLUE.
IT'S A 180-DEGREE TURN.
>> YOU GUYS WANT TO READ YOUR
LETTERS?
>> YEAH, ANDREA SAID SHE WANTED
TO DO THAT, TOO.
WE CAN ALL SIT TOGETHER.
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M ON TOP OF THE
WORLD RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE LETTERS FROM HOME.
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING THINKING
"I'LL GIVE ANYTHING FOR A PIZZA.
I'D GIVE ANYTHING FOR A
HAMBURGER."
MY MOM, MY MOM, MY MOM.
AND WHEN THIS CAME OUT IT WAS
LIKE, THAT'S IT.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
SO MUCH ENCOURAGEMENT AND SO
MUCH LOVE.
THIS IS ALL THAT MATTERS.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD, HUH?
GOOD.
>> THIS IS WHY I'M OUT HERE.
FOR THESE PEOPLE.
I'LL DO ANYTHING FOR THEM.
>> YOU OKAY OVER THERE, COCHRAN.
>> YEAH, I'M GOOD.
>> YOU'RE JUST EMOTIONAL.
>> YEAH, WHICH IS SURPRISING FOR
ME.
>> I KNOW, I REMEMBER LAST TIME.
>> I'VE BEEN TRYING HARD TO PLAY
THIS EMOTIONLESS GAME THIS TIME,
JUST BE A GAME BOT WHO RUNS
THROUGH STRATEGY.
AND GETTING LETTERS FROM HOME
MAKES YOU REALIZE THERE IS LIFE
OUTSIDE THE GAME AND THING I
HAVE MORE THAN THIS GAME.
AND PART OF ME IS A LITTLE BIT
HAPPY THAT I'M STILL THE PERSON
WHO VALUES FAMILY AND LOVE AND I
GUESS THE THINGS THAT ARE REALLY
IMPORTANT.
I FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT, THOUGH.
>> JeffWHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> OH, MY GOSH, STOP.
IT'S A BIG DEAL.
28 DAYS WITHOUT HEARING FROM
YOUR FAMILY.
>> IT'S GOOD, MAN, IT MEANS
YOU'RE HUMAN.
>> YOU'RE HANGING TOUGH THERE,
GIRL.
YOU HAVEN'T GOTTEN ANYTHING
DECENT TO EAT OF SUBSTANCE IN --
>> 29 DAYS.
>> THAT'S INSANE.
KEEP HANGING TOUGH, AND STICK
WITH US.
>> YOU BETTER PUT SOMETHING OUT
YOUR BUTT, GOOD.
>> IF WE HAVE ERIK AND WE HAD
YOU, THAT'S A MAJORITY.
>> IT'S GUARANTEE TO THE FINAL
FIVE.
>> MALCOLM HAS THE CLUE FOR THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY AND EVERYBODY'S
PARANOID BECAUSE IF THEY'RE
CONSTANTLY WINNING AND HAVE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS YOU START
FEELING THEY'RE UNBEATABLE.
SO IF YOU CAN'T BEAT THEM, JOIN
THEM.
>> WE'RE GOING TO WIN PERSONAL
IMMUNITIES AND HAVE THE IDOLS.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW THIS.
>> SO WE COULD GUARANTEE YOU
WORST CASE FIFTH AND WE WANT
YOU.
>> FIRST ROUND DRAFT PICK.
>> WE NEED TO TALK.
>> NOT RIGHT NOW, THOUGH.
>> UH-HUH.
>> THEY STILL HAVE US
OUTNUMBERED 6-3.
BUT IF WE HAVE ERIK AND SHERRI,
WE ARE THE MAJORITY.
>> THINK WE'LL BE ABLE TO GET
THEM?
>> YEAH, LET ME DEAL WITH IT.
YOU DEAL WITH ERIK, I'LL DEAL
WITH SHERRI.
>> WE NEED TO KNOCK OUT COCHRAN.
IF WE KNOCK OUT STRATEGIC POWER
PLAYERS THAT ALLIANCE IS
COMPLETELY BUSTED.
>> I'M STILL TRYING TO STICK
AROUND.
MAKING IT JUST A COUPLE MORE
DAYS IN THIS GAME CAN CHANGE THE
GAME.
THE IDOL CLUE SAID IF YOU WALK
TOWARD THE WATER-- WHICH I'M
ASSUMING MEANS THE WELL-- YOU
HAVE TO LOOK TO YOUR LEFT AND
THERE'S GOING TO BE A TREE
GROWING OUT OF THE ROCKS AND
SOMEWHERE AROUND THE BASE SIX
INCHES DEEP IS A BURIED HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO I'VE GOT A LITTLE BIT OF
DIGGING TO DO AND HOPEFULLY I'LL
HAVE MY THIRD IDOL IN THIS GAME.
AT THIS POINT ANY POWER THAT I
CAN GET IN MY CORNER IS GOING TO
BE NECESSARY TO ENSURING I STICK
AROUND.
MORNING.
>> OH, HEY.
I LOVE THE SMELL OF FRESH DIRT.
>> YEAH, ME, TOO.
>> WENT OVER AND STARTED DIGGING
FOR THE IDOL AND GOT BUSTED BY
ANDREA.
SHE SAW ME CHECKING OUT A FEW
OTHER CONSPICUOUS ROCKS AND
LARGE TREES.
IT'S A WEIRD SITUATION.
>> I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM,
I'M SORRY.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
I'M JUST GOING TO RELAX.
>> I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
>> THIS MORNING I WOKE UP AND
MALCOLM IS ALREADY STIRRING AND
IT'S STILL DARK AND I FOLLOWED
THEM TO THE WELL AND I FIND HIM
DIGGING AT THIS TREE AND THEN I
DECIDED TO JUST SIT HERE BECAUSE
I KNOW THAT IF F THERE'S AN IDOL
IT'S PROBABLY ME GOING HOME
BECAUSE MY NAME HAS COME ALREADY
AND SO IT WAS A SHOWDOWN.
IS THIS A STANDOFF?
>> YOU'RE JUST GOING TO SIT
HERE?
>> I'M JUST GOING TO COME BACK
LATER.
ARE YOU GOING TO FOLLOW ME
AROUND ALL DAY?
ARE YOU NOT LEAVING?
>> I WAS GOING TO STAY HERE.
I MEAN, YOU CAN DO WHAT YOU NEED
TO DO, LIKE, I'M NOT GOING TO
DISTURB ANYTHING.
>> IF I LEAVE, ARE YOU LEAVING
WITH ME?
>> I'LL GO BACK WITH YOU.
>> RIGHT NOW?
>> WELL I CAN'T -- YEAH.
YOU'RE LIKE A LITTLE SISTER I
CAN'T GET RID OF.
>> (LAUGHS)
>> OKAY, LET'S GO.
SAME TIME TOMORROW MORNING.
>> YEAH, I'LL SEE YOU HERE.
HOPEFULLY.
ANDREA, SHE'S A SMART GIRL,
SHE'S NOT GOING TO GIVE ME A
SECOND TO DIG.
I FEEL LIKE A BIT OF AN IDIOT.
$480 DOWN THE DRAIN.
A MILLION DOLLARS DOWN THE
DRAIN, MAYBE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
REYNOLD, GOT TO TAKE IT BACK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO HOLD ON TO A ROPE THAT
IS CONNECTED TO A VERY HEAVY
LOG.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS YOU WILL
MOVE ONE KNOT LOWER ON THE ROPE,
MAKING THE WEIGHT MORE DIFFICULT
TO BEAR.
WHEN YOU DROP YOUR ROPE, YOU'RE
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WOMENS
IMPUNITY, WILL GO INTO TRIBAL
COUNCIL SAFE AND GUARANTEED A
1-8 SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
EVERYBODY ELSE VULNERABLE.
SOMEBODY WILL BE GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
COCHRAN, AT THE AUCTION YOU
BOUGHT AN ADVANTAGE.
GO AHEAD AND OPEN IT UP AND READ
IT TO THE GROUP.
>> "AT ANY POINT IN THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE YOU MAY MOVE YOUR HAND
UP TWO KNOTS, GIVING YOU A
SIGNIFICANT ADVANTAGE."
I NEED TO WIN TODAY REALLY
BADLY, BUT COCHRAN GOT A GAME
ADVANTAGE BUT COCHRAN IS BY NO
MEANS ANY TYPE OF PHYSICAL
THREAT WHATSOEVER SO I FEEL VERY
OPTIMISTIC.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY
TAKE YOUR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
DECIDE WHICH HAND YOU WANT TO
START HOLDING WITH AND I'M GOING
TO COUNT YOU IN.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
THIS CHALLENGE IS OFFICIALLY ON.
EVERYBODY HERE IS HOLDING
ONE-THIRD OF THE BODY WEIGHT
THAT YOU STARTED THIS GAME WITH.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN THIS SPOT
FOR FIVE MINUTES THEN WE'LL MOVE
DOWN ANOTHER KNOT.
HERE WE GO.
START MAKING THAT RAN THE SEUGS.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE DOWN TO THE
SECOND KNOT.
EVERYBODY LOOKING GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO MUFF ONE MORE
KNOT DOWN NOW.
MAKE YOUR MOVE.
>> I'M USING MY ADVANTAGE.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
COCHRAN HAS ELECTED TO TAKE HIS
TWO-KNOT ADVANTAGE AND USE IT
NOW WHICH MEANS COCHRAN MOVES
BACK UP TO THE TOP OF THE ROPE.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS HOLDING A LOT
MORE WEIGHT THAN HE IS.
YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP DROPPING
DOWN EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE DOWN ONE
MORE KNOT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY MAKE YOUR
MOVE.
ONE MORE KNOT DOWN.
HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY MOVE DOWN ONE MORE
KNOT.
THIS IS THE LAST KNOT YOU HAVE
TO HOLD ON TO.
AFTER THIS ROUND IT WILL JUST BE
A LITTLE PIECE OF ROPE.
NOW IT'S GETTING VERY HEAVY.
BRENDA STEPS OFF AND IS THE
FIRST ONE OUT.
WE'RE DOWN TO EIGHT.
ERIK DROPS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO SEVEN.
YOU SAW HOW QUICKLY IT CAN BE
OVER.
DIG!
YOU'VE BEEN OUT HERE 30 DAYS.
YOU DO NOT WANT TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
DAWN'S STRUGGLING TO STAY IN IT.
KEEP DIGGING, DAWN.
LESS THAN A MINUTE LEFT IN THIS
ROUND.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
HERE WE GO.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE DOWN TO THE
NEXT POSITION ON THE ROPE IN
THIS LAST ROUND.
THERE WILL BE NO KNOT UNDERNEATH
YOU.
NOW IT'S JUST ROPE-- EXCEPT FOR
COCHRAN.
THAT TWO-KNOT ADVANTAGE COMING
INTO PLAY.
SHERRI CAN'T DO IT.
SHERRI'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO SIX.
JUST LIKE THAT, MALCOLM'S OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO FIVE.
THE SUN MAKES YOU SWEAT, THAT
SWEAT MAKES THE ROPE SLIPPERY.
AS ANDREA'S FINDING OUT RIGHT
NOW.
SHE CAN'T HOLD ON ANY LONGER.
WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR.
>> THIS IS HARD!
>> Jeff: COME ON, DAWN!
DIG, WOMAN!
REYNOLD, KEEP DIGGING, COCHRAN,
HANG IN THERE.
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> Jeff: EDDIE, YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH MUCH TOUGHER, BROTHER.
>> OH, MOTHER!
>> Jeff: DAWN REALLY DIGGING!
DAWN CANNOT HANG ON ANY LONGER.
>> NICE JOB, DAWN.
>> Jeff: GREAT EFFORT BUT DAWN
IS OUT AND WE'RE DOWN TO THREE
GUYS.
REYNOLD ON ONE END, EDDIE ON THE
OTHER, CONGRESS FLAN THE MIDDLE.
>> UH-OH.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD'S STARTING TO
SLIP.
MUSCLES TWITCHING.
REYNOLD IS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS A SHOWDOWN!
HOLD ON.
>> I'M TRYING.
MY HAND'S NOT --
>> Jeff: COCHRAN HAS A TWO
KNOT ADVANTAGE.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING TO HOLD ON
TO.
EDDIE DOESN'T.
YOU BOTH NEED TO DIG!
>> FOCUS, JUST FOCUS.
EDDIE STARTING TO SLIP.
HE'S GOT TO HANG ON.
>> HOLD IT, EDDIE.
>> Jeff: HE CAN NOT!
EDDIE'S OUT.
COCHRAN WINS IMMUNITY!
>> COCHRAN!
>> WOW.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, COME ON
OVER.
(APPLAUSE)
>> COCHRAN, WAY TO GO.
>> Jeff: YOU EVEN GOT A
VICTORY RUN
IT JUST HASN'T LOST ITS THRILL.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN WITH HIS
SECOND INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
GUARANTEED A 1-8 SHOT AT WINNING
THIS GAME.
FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> COCHRAN'S SAFE FOR ANOTHER
DAY SO I'D LIKE TO THINK I'VE
INFUSED SOME SORT OF
REVOLUTIONARY
SPIRIT IN THESE GUYS AND
THEY'LL REALIZE AT NINE THE
THREE OF US CAN BE HELP TO
SOMEBODY TRYING TO SHAKE THINGS
UP.
>> Jeff: I AM THE GREATER
CHALLENGER IN "SURVIVOR"
CARAMOAN.
I'M DEMOLISHING EVERYBODY.
I'VE WON HALF THE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES.
I'M THE GUY THAT WAS SCREAMED AT
AFTER EVERY CHALLENGE I PLAYED
BECAUSE I'M SUCH A LIABILITY, I
SUCK AT CHALLENGES, I'M WEAK.
BUT NOW I AM THE BIGGEST
CHALLENGE THREAT IN THIS GAME
AND I DON'T CARE IF IT MAKES ME
A THREAT.
I'M JUST GOING TO KEEP WINNING.
>> I'M NERVOUS.
IDOLS DRIVE YOU CRAZY OUT HERE.
I FOUND TWO WITHOUT CLUES AND
NOW I CAN'T FIND THE ONE THAT I
PAID $480 FOR A CLUE TO AND I
CAN'T GO LOOK FOR IT BECAUSE
I'LL JUST BE HOUNDED BY THE
GIRLS.
THEY'LL START DIGGING AROUND ME
LITERALLY.
I'VE JUST GOT TO BLUFF MY WAY
THROUGH THIS BASICALLY.
>> WE NEED THEM TO THINK WE'RE
PLAYING AN IDOL.
>> DID YOU GET IT.
>> NO.
>> WE CAN'T LET THEM VOTE SIX.
THEY HAVE TO BE CONVINCED WE'RE
GOING TO PLAY THE IDOL TODAY.
>> IF THE FAVORITES GO A SPLIT
VOTE, THAT'S THE BEST-CASE
SCENARIO BECAUSE I BELIEVE WE'VE
GOT SHERRI AND IF I HAVE SHERRI
AND THEY SPLIT THE VOTE NO
MATTER HOW THEY PLAY IT, 3-3,
WE'RE GOOD WITH FOUR VOTES.
I TRUST YOU AND I LIKE YOU SO
THEY HAVE TO SPLIT THE VOTE
BECAUSE I GOT THE IDOL.
>> YOU HAVE ONE IDOL?
>> SO NO MATTER WHAT THEY HAVE
TO SPLIT THE VOTE OR ELSE I CAN
PLAY THAT THING.
ARE WE GOING TO MAKE A DEAL OR
NOT, SORRY?
I'LL GO TO THE END WITH YOU
RIGHT NOW.
I'M TELLING YOU.
>> BUT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
GET RID OF ONE OF THEM.
>> I KNOW.
>> I THINK I WANT TO PLAY WITH
THE MUSCLE HEADS BECAUSE I THINK
THE MUSCLE HEADS ARE GOING TO
KEEP WINNING THE CHALLENGES.
BUT THEN I FLIP AND I GO, BUT
COCHRAN WON ONE TODAY.
BUT COCHRAN WON ONE BECAUSE HE
HAS AN ADVANTAGE.
>> ERIK?
>> HE'S OVER THERE TALKING.
>> NO BUT HE'S GOING TO BE FIVE.
>> IF YOU'RE WITH US THAT'S GOOD
AS LONG AS THEY KNOW I HAVE AN
IDOL.
>> WHO ARE WE GOING TO GO FOR?
I NEED TO KNOW THE NAME.
>> ANDREA.
>> SWEAR TO ME.
>> PINKIE?
>> IF WE'RE FOUR WITH YOU, WE'RE
ON OUR WAY.
>> YOU CAN TAKE DOWN ANYBODY YOU
WANT.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T CARE WHO IT
IS AS LONG AS IT'S NOT ONE OF
THE FOUR OF US.
>> IF THEY'RE GOING TO SPLIT THE
VOTE 3-3, ASSUMING 3-3, ME BEING
ONE OF THE THREE IN THAT.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'LL VOTE WITH YOU GUYS.
>> OKAY.
>> AND IT WILL BE FOUR.
>> COOL.
>> THERE ARE TWO ALLIANCES WHICH
ARE THE THREE BOYS OF MALCOLM,
EDDIE AND REYNOLD AND THEN THE
FIVE FAVORITES AND SHERRI ON THE
OTHER SIDE.
I NEED TO KNOW AS MUCH
INFORMATION AS POSSIBLE.
SO I HAVE TO KEEP PLAYING BOTH
SIDES WHICH I'M EXCITED ABOUT
BUT AT THE SAME TIME I'M
TERRIFIED.
>> I TRUST YOU.
IT'S JUST A BIG VOTE.
>> I KNOW IT'S A BIG VOTE.
>> BECAUSE IF SOMEONE SWINGS.
>> BUT WE'VE NOT GOING TO FLIP
BECAUSE EVERYBODY'S SOLID.
>> I PUT ALL MY TRUST IN YOU.
>> I KNOW.
WE ALL ARE.
I KNOW.
>> IF I DIDN'T HAVE DIARRHEA I
WOULDN'T BE SO NERVOUS.
IT'S JUST THAT I'M PUTTING MY
WHOLE GAME IN WITH YOU.
>> DAWN, I KNOW!
THIS IS THE BIGGEST DECISION FOR
ME TODAY.
THERE'S A FORK IN THE ROAD, YOU
CAN'T GO BACK AFTER THIS.
I HAVE TO KEEP PLAYING LIKE I'M
GOING BOTH WAYS AT THE SAME TIME
ALL THE WAY UP UNTIL THE VOTE.
ALL THE WAY UP UNTIL I KNOW THE
NAME I'M ABOUT TO WRITE DOWN AND
IT MIGHT EVEN CHANGE AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> WHAT'S THE VOTE TONIGHT?
GUYS AND YOU VOTE FOR MALCOLM.
>> GIRLS VOTE REYNOLD.
NO IDOLS PLAYED.
MALCOLM GOES HOME.
>> I'D LOVE FOR MALCOLM TO GO
HOME.
>> YOU GUYS ARE ALL REALLY
COMFORTABLE WITH SPLITTING?
>> PART OF ME THINKS THAT WHY
WOULDN'T YOU JUST DO A STRAIGHT
VOTE ON SOMEBODY?
>> WHY WOULD WE?
MALCOLM HAS THE --
>> YEAH, BUT THEY'LL STILL PLAY
IT IF WE'RE DOING A STRAIGHT
VOTE.
>> THAT'S MY POINT.
>> IT'S SAFE IF IT'S SPLIT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> WELL, IT'S DISASTROUS IF IT'S
SPLIT AND SOMETHING GOES WRONG
WITH THE SPLIT.
>> RIGHT.
>> THE ONLY SUSPICIOUS IS THAT
MAYBE ERIK CASTING THE PHILLIP
VOTE.
BUT WHAT WOULD BE THE POINT OF
DOING THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> IF ALL GOES AS PLANNED MY
ALLIANCE IS GOING TO VOTE WITH
ME.
BUT ALL IT TAKES IS ONE PERSON
TO FLIP.
IT'S HARD!
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, PUTTING YOUR
FAITH INTO THESE PEOPLE THAT,
YOU KNOW, AS MUCH AS I THINK
THAT ERIK'S TELLING THE TRUTH I
DON'T KNOW IF HE HAS A DIFFERENT
AGENDA.
LIKE, IF HE WANTS TO COME TO
THIS GAME AND SAY "I GOT FOOLED
BY A GIRL THE FIRST TIME, WHY
DON'T I JUST FLIP WITH THE
GUYS?"
I THINK ERIK'S WITH US.
I MEAN, I DON'T THINK ERIK'S
DUMB ENOUGH TO SWITCH OVER RIGHT
NOW.
YOU KNOW, HOW DUMB WOULD YOU BE
TO DO THAT?
>> SIX FAVORITES, THREE AMIGOS.
NEITHER SIDE REALIZES THIS IS MY
GAME RIGHT NOW.
I'M THE ONE CALLING THE SHOTS.
THEY DON'T GET IT.
>> I WANT TO TALK TO YOU FOR A
SECOND.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
I KIND OF WANT HIM TO THINK I
DON'T REALIZE I HAVE THIS MUCH
POWER.
AS OF THIS MOMENT RIGHT NOW I'M
TORN OF WHO I'M GOING WITH.
>> I'LL NOW BRING IN THE MEMBERS
OF OUR JURY.
MICHAEL AND PHILLIP VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOTS TO TALK ABOUT, REYNOLD, DID
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL AND
EVERYTHING THAT WENT ON SHAKE
ANYTHING UP?
>> I THINK PHILLIP'S DEPARTURE
MARKED A NEW CHAPTER IN THE GAME
AND I DON'T NECESSARILY SEE 6-3
ANYMORE BECAUSE IN THIS GAME IF
YOU DON'T MAKE MOVES YOU MIGHT
BE DOOMED TO BE GOING HOME
SOONER THAN YOU THOUGHT.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, A LITTLE
UNNERVING WHEN YOU HEAR ONE OF
THE THREE GUYS WHO'VE BEEN ON
THE OUTS SAY "NOT SO SURE IT'S
6-3 ANYMORE."
>> THAT'S SOMETHING THAT MAKES
ME NERVOUS.
BUT ANYBODY FLIPPING AT THIS
POINT WOULD BE PRETTY MUCH
DOOMING THEIR GAME.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT EDDIE,
MALCOLM, AND REYNOLD WHO ARE
GOING TO DOMINATE EVERY
CHALLENGE --
>> Jeff: SO FAR COCHRAN'S WON
50%.
>> OKAY, BESIDES COCHRAN.
THEY'VE MADE IT CLEAR THAT
THEY'RE STICKING TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: BUT SHERRI, THE
RATIONALE COULD BE I'M NOT
GETTING TO THE END WITH THE SIX
BECAUSE I ALREADY FEEL LIKE I'M
ON THE BOTTOM.
>> ABSOLUTELY THAT'S CROSSED MY
MIND.
WHO KNOWS WHERE I SIT WITH THE
FAVORITES?
>> Jeff: DAWN, DOES THAT
CONCERN YOU?
>> YEAH, I WAS ACTUALLY LIKE,
OH, SHERRI!
I THINK THAT EVERYBODY FEELS
VULNERABLE AND A LOT OF TIMES
YOU'RE MAKING DECISIONS BECAUSE
YOU'RE THINKING "IT'S ME ON THE
BOTTOM.
IT'S ME ON THE BOTTOM."
AND I THINK IN SHERRI'S CASE I
HOPE SHE'S NOT THINKING SHE'S ON
THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, AT THE
AUCTION YOU BOUGHT WHAT WAS
LABELED INFORMATION IN THE GAME.
DID YOU FEEL OTHERS WONDERING
WHAT THAT INFORMATION WAS?
>> YEAH, IT WAS A LITTLE CRAZY
AROUND CAMP, YOU KNOW?
IT WAS MY EYES ONLY BUT EVERYONE
HERE'S CURIOUS.
IT WAS A FUN DAY.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, WHAT WAS THE
SPECULATION?
>> I THINK MOST OF US THOUGHT
THIS WAS A CLUE TO THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND I'M 80% SURE
HE HAS IT.
>> Jeff: DAWN, WHY SO MUCH
CONCERN AND FEAR AROUND THE
IDOL?
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE GETTING
PLAYED SO OFTEN!
I THINK IT'S JUST THIS
REINTRODUCTION.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF THEM.
YOU'VE BEEN PLAYING THEM.
>> WE'RE MAKING IT RAIN.
>> THEY'RE WORKING!
>> Jeff: HOW CONCERNED ARE YOU
THAT SOMEBODY WITHIN THE SIX
MIGHT BE FLIPPING TONIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH.
I MEAN, IT'S TEMPTING, OH, IF I
FEEL LIKE I'M WORRIED I SHOULD
TRADE UP FOR A NEW ALLIANCE.
WE'VE SEEN IT HAPPEN IN OTHER
SEASONS OF "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: SO, COCHRAN, ANOTHER
OPTION IS SOMEBODY FROM THIS
GROUP FLIPS AND JOINS EDDIE,
MALCOLM, AND REYNOLD.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, JUST HYPE
HYPOTHETICALLY THREE VOTES
EDDIE, THREE VOTES MALL COMM.
THOSE GUYS ARE VOTING TOGETHER
AS A THREESOME.
THAT MEANS ALL IT TAKES IS ONE
OF THE THREE OF THE SIX TO JUMP
OVER TO THAT THREESOME AND
SUDDENLY THEY'RE A FOURSOME,
THAT'S WHERE THINGS GET
EXCITING.
AND THEN THEY CAN KICK OUT
WHOEVER THEY WANT.
AND IF THAT PERSON WHO FLIPPED
OVER TO THE THREE, SIX OF THOSE
THREE, THEN IT'S 4-4 AND IT'S A
WHOLE NEW GAME.
>> Jeff: SO ANDREA, HOW MUCH
FEAR DOES IT PUT INTO YOU AS YOU
GET READY TO VOTE?
>> I'M NERVOUS.
I'M SURE I'M BEING TARGETED
TONIGHT SO THERE WILL PROBABLY
BE VOTES GOING MY WAY BUT I
THINK IT'S IMPORTANT THAT YOU DO
TRUST THE GROUP OF PEOPLE YOU'RE
WITH.
>> Jeff: IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
BRENDA, YOU'RE UP.
>> I'M JUST HOPING ONE OF YOU
THREE GUYS GOES HOME.
>> I REALLY HOPE YOU DON'T HAVE
THAT IDOL BECAUSE VOTING YOU OFF
WOULD JUST BE SO DELICIOUS IT
WOULD BE INDESCRIBABLY
DELICIOUS.
IT WOULD JUST BE --
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, REYNOLD.
MALCOLM.
ANDREA.
ONE VOTE EACH, REYNOLD, MALCOLM,
REYNOLD, MALCOLM.
ANDREA, WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
TWO VOTES EACH FOR REYNOLD,
MALCOLM, AND ANDREA.
REYNOLD, THAT'S THREE VOTES
REYNOLD.
ANDREA, WE'RE TIED THREE VOTES
REYNOLD, THREE VOTES ANDREA, TWO
VOTES MALCOLM, ONE VOTE LEFT.
MALCOLM.
WE HAVE A THREE-WAY TIE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO
RELOAD.
REYNOLD, MALCOLM AND ANDREA, YOU
WON'T VOTE.
EVERYONE ELSE YOU CAN ONLY VOTE
FOR ONE OF THOSE THREE.
ERIK, COME GRAB THIS.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
MALCOLM.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
MALCOLM, THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S
ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> OH, DAMN IT.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> BEST OF LUCK, GUYS.
>> BYE, MALCOLM!
>> .
>> SEE YA.
>> I NEED A DRINK!
>> Jeff: WELL, REYNOLD AND
EDDIE, YOU'VE BEEN ON THE
OUTSIDE OF THIS GAME SINCE DAY
ONE AND 30 DAYS LATER NOTHING
HAS CHANGED.
BUT YOU'RE STILL ALIVE AND
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS FOR
ANYBODY TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR" -- ONE PERSON IS
WALKING OUT OF HERE WITH
IMMUNITY.
REYNOLD, THE BIGGEST THREAT IN
THE GAME TRIES TO HOLD ON FOR
DEAR LIFE.
REYNOLD, ANOTHER INCREDIBLE
RECOVERY!
BUT HE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE IN
TROUBLE.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK SHOULD GO
FIRST?
BRENDA OR DAWN?
>> I THINK TODAY IS THE
BEGINNING OF THE END FOR THE
ALLIANCE OF SIX.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S BEEN A GREAT RIDE.
I SPENT $480 ON AN IDOL CLUE AND
DIDN'T FIND THE IDOL.
I FOUND TWO WITHOUT PAYING AND
CAN'T FIND THE ONE I PAY FOR.
PROBABLY GOING GET A LITTLE
MOCKING AFTER THIS BUT I
WOULDN'T HAVE PLAYED IT TONIGHT
ANYWAYS.
I THOUGHT I WAS SAFE.
IT JUST SHOWS YOU AS SOON AS YOU
THINK YOU'VE FIGURED IT OUT
YOU'RE GOING HOME AND TONIGHT
WAS MY TIME.
I GOT BURNED PRETTY BAD.