>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": ALTHOUGH STEALTH "R"
US HAS HAD CONTROL OF THE GAME,
THEY ARE FAR FROM A WELL-OILED
MACHINE.
DAWN HAS STRUGGLETO CONTROL HER
EMOTIONS.
>> IT IS KIND OF FUNNY THAT I
CRY SO MUCH.
>> Jeff: ANDREA HAS BEEN
COURTING THE ENEMY.
>> I CAN AT LEAST GUARANTEE NEXT
VOTE WON'T BE YOU.
>> Jeff: AND PHILLIP'S
LEADERSHIP STYLE HAS WORN THIN
AMONGST HIS RIVALS AND ALES.
THE'S ONLY ONE REQUIREMENT
TO BELONG TO STEALTH "R" US, YOU
MUST BE LOYAL AND ABSOLUTELY
TRUSTWORTHY.
>> IT'S ALL CRAZY.
THEY'RE ALL CRAZY OUT HERE.
>> WELCOME TO THE ORGANIZATION.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE-- ANDREA IS OUT,
BRENDA WINS IMMUNITY.
BRENDA HELD ON FOR THE WIN AND
STEALTH "R" US SAW A CHANCE TO
TAKE OUT MALCOLM AIR, FORME ALLY
TRYING TO DESTROY THEIR
ALLIANCE.
>> AFTER ANDREA CAUGHT WIND SHE
MAY BE IN TROUBLE--
>> IT'S BEEN TALKED ABOUT.
>> ME?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: SHE TRIED TO CONVINCE
HER ALLIANCE TO PLAY IT SAFE BY
VOTING OUT MICHAEL.
>> THE SAFEST BET EEFORT WOULD
BE MICHAEL.
>> I STILL LIKE MALCOLM.
>> I KNOW, BUT I THINK I'M BEING
TARGETED.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL--
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND WANTS TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> HOLD UP.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM FELT THE HEAT
AND CONVINCED REYNOLD TO GIVE UP
HIS IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> THEY ALL VOTED FOR ME.
>> Jeff: BUT HE WAS WRONG, AND
MICHAEL WAS SENT HOME.
MICHAEL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
10 ARE LEFT WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT?
>> THERE'S NO FIRE.
>> I KNOW.
>> THAT SUCKS.
>> I WAS THINKING, WE SHOULD
HAVE A MEETING.
>> EVERYBODY LEAVING?
>> YEAH, WE'RE ASKING TO BE BACK
IN A SECOND?
>> EVERYBODY IS GOING EXCEPT FOR
US.
>> I'LL HANG OUT WITH YOU GUYS.
>> WELCOME TO THE BOTTOM.
>> IT WAS RIGHT CALL.
I DON'T FEEL TOO BAD ABOUT IT.
>> IT'S ACTUALLY NOT THAT BAD TO
BE DOWN HERE.
WE HAVE NOTHING TO REALLY BE
AFRAID OF.
>> THAT'S RIGHT TRUE.
>> NOBODY TALKS BEHIND OUR BACKS
BECAUSE WE'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
>> JUST ABOUT EVERYTHING I TRIED
TO DO WENT WRONG.
I TRIED TO BRING IN THE PERSON
WHO I THOUGHT WAS ON THE BOTTOM,
DAWN.
DAWN WAS NEVER WITH ME.
PHILLIP GAVE THAT AWAY AT TRIBAL
TONIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS THE MOST HELLISH DAY
FOR ME.
>> I THINK MY DOUBLE AGENT DAYS
ARE OVER.
>> THEY HAVE NO IDOL.
EVEN IF THEY HAVE ONE IDOL, WE
CAN SPLIT IT.
WE CAN SPLIT IT.
>> THEY HAVE NO IDOL.
>> EXACTLY.
THAT'S WHAT WE JUST SAID.
>> TOMORROW WE'RE GOING TO FIND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> TOMORROW WE HAVE TO WAKE UP
AND SEARCH.
IF THERE'S ANY SILVER LINING, I
STILL HAVE AN IDOL.
I STILL HAVE SOME POWER, JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
I'M NOT GOING DOWN WITHOUT
FIREWORKS.
>> WE MIGHT BE AT THE BOTTOM BUT
WE'RE NOT GOING DOWN NEXT.
>> I MIGHT BE.
>> I'D RATHER BY MY OWN MAN THAN
BE A PUPPET FOR PHILLIP.
I DON'T THINK THAT NECESSARILY
IS THE CASE.
SHE'S A BETRAYED A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
>> AND SHE'S, ALSO, UM... SHE'S
REALLY NOT A THREAT IN ANY OF
THE CHALLENGES.
>> BRENDA!
I NEED YOU QUICK!
>> HURRY!
>> RUN!
>> WHAT DID SHE SAY?
>> BRENDA.
>> PLEASE.
>> WHO'S YELLING?
>> DAWN?
>> SHE SAID, "COME HERE,
PLEASE."
BUT, LIKE-.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHAT'S WRONG?
>> THIS IS SO EMBARRASSING.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> I GOT HIT IN THE MOUTH A
WHILE AGO AND I LOST MY BOTTOM
TEETH AND I HAVE A RETAINER THAT
HAS THE TEETH ON THEM AND I TOOK
A GULP OF WATER AND THEY CAME
OUT AND I KNOW I HAVE THEM, AND
I NEED A MASK.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> I NEED THEM NOW.
I HAVE'S RIITARIAN THAT HAS SOME
TEETH IN THE FRONT THAT I HAD
LOST.
I GOT HIT AND LOST THEM.
AND I WAS IN THE WATER, AND I
OPENED MY MOUTH TO GET A SCOOP
OF WATER AND IT CAME OUT, AND I
THINK IT'S RIGHT THERE BUT I
CAN'T SEE.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE ELSE TO
KNOW.
THANKS, BRENDA.
I WON'T GO TO THE CHALLENGE.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
I'LL PULL MYSELF FROM THE GAME.
>> CAN YOU SEE IT?
>> HANG ON.
>> I'M GOING TO PULL MYSELF IF I
DON'T FIND IT.
I'M PULLING MYSELF.
PLEASE GET DOWN THERE.
OH, MY GOD!
BRENDA!
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
SO THANK GOODNESS FOR BRENDA.
THERE IS A LOT OF KINDNESS, EVEN
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING A GAME
THAT'S ABOUT ONE WINNER.
SO THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD REMINDER
RIGHT NOW.
OH, MY GOSH!
I'M SORRY.
OH, MY GOSH.
YOU JUST SAVED ME.
>> I HEART JUST WENT OUT TO HER
SO MUCH.
AND AFTER THAT INCIDENT, I'M NOT
GOING TO TURN MY BACK ON HER.
>> I REALLY LOVE YOU, BRENDA.
THANK YOU FOR HELPING ME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'LL BE DIVIDED INTO TWO TEAMS
OF FIVE.
ON MY GO, ONE PERSON FROM EACH
TEAM WILL RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES INTO A MUDDY PIT,
WHERE YOU WILL SEARCH FOR A BAG
OF BALLS. ONCE YOU HAVE THE
BALLS, YOU'LL GO THROUGH THE
RICE, DROP YOUR BAG ON THE TABLE
AND SHE THEN THE NEXT PERSON
GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL FIVE
BAGS, YOU WILL THEN SHOOT YOUR
BALLS INTO YOUR BASKET.
FIRST TEAM TO GET ALL 12 BECAUSE
INTO THEIR BARKET WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
THE WINNING TEAM OF FIVE WILL BE
TAKEN TO A VERY NICE RESORT WITH
A BEAUTIFUL POOL.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: AND A NICE LUNCH.
BEEF, CHICKEN, PORK, COCKTAILS.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: MARGARITAS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS HUGE.
>> Jeff: NICE BREAK FROM THE
GAME AND YOU RETURN BACK TO
CAMP.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: WE'LL DRAW FOR
SPORTS, AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS
OF FIVE.
RUNNING FOR PURPLE WE'VE GOT
REYNOLD, ERIK, DAWN, COCHRAN,
AND PHILLIP.
RUNNING FOR ORANGE WE HAVE
EDDIE, MALCOLM, SHERRY, ANDREA,
AND BRENDA.
HERE WE GO FOR A NICE REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST STEP IS OVER THAT BEAM.
MALCOLM AND ERIK FLYING ACROSS
IT.
NO PROBLEM.
NOW TO THE WATER SLIDE AND INTO
THE MUD.
STILL NEXT AND NECK.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A BAG IN THAT
PIT.
ONCE YOU FIND THE BAG OF BALLS,
YOU CAN MOVE ON.
ERIK'S GOT HIS.
HE'S MOVING ON.
MALCOLM STILL WORKING ON THE BAG
FOR HIS TEAM.
ERIK DIGGING THROUGH THAT RICE,
MAKING A BIG PASSAGEWAY FOR ALL
OF HIS TRIBES MATES.
MALCOLM STILL IN THE MUD PIT
WITH A DIFFERENT STRATEGY.
HE'S LOOKING FOR ALL HIS TEAM'S
BAGS AT ONCE.
NOW ERIK IS GOING TO HEAD
THROUGH WITH THAT FIRST BAG
COVERED IN RICE.
GO, PURPLE!
REYNOLD NOW ON THE COURSE FOR
PURPLE.
>> WHOOO!
LET'S GO, REYNOLD.
>> MALCOLM, HOW YOU MAKING OUT,
BUDDY?
>> Jeff: REYNOLD NOW IN THE
MUD PIT FOR THE PURPLE.
>> FINDS A COUPLE, REYNOLD.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD NOW GOING TO
START LOOKING FOR EXTRA BAGS,
TAKING THE SAME STRATEGY MALCOLM
IS DOING AND HE'S GOT A SECONDS
ONE.
MALCOLM HAS A FOURTH BAG.
>> KEEP GOING, COME ON.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD HAS A THIRD
BAG FOR HIS TEAM.
REYNOLD HAS ALL THE BAGS
UNCOVERED.
HUGE ADVANTAGE NEW FOR
PURPOSELE.
GO, UPPER PEL!
DAWN NOW ON THE COURSE FOR
PURPLE.
MALCOLM HAS FOUND ALL THE BAGS
FOR HIS TEAM, BUT PURPLE WITH A
BIG, EARLY LEAD.
DAWN NOW ON THE SLIDE.
FACE FIRST INTO THE MUD.
BIG HIT.
MALCOLM'S THERE, GO, ORANGE!
ANDREA ON THE COURSE FOR THE
ORANGE TEAM NOW.
FLYING ACROSS THAT BALANCE BEAM.
DAWN, THANKS TO REYNOLD'S WORK,
CAN JUST PICK UP A BAG AND KEEP
MOVING.
PURP CELL ON A ROLL.
>> COME OCOME ON!
>> Jeff: GO, PURPLE!
COCHRAN NOW ON THE COURSE.
ANDREA NOW INTO THE MUD.
THERE'S A BAG READY FOR HER,
THANKS TO MALCOLM.
ANDREA THROUGH THE RICE.
TRYING TO TIGHTEN IT UP.
GO, ORANGE!
SHERRY NOW ON THE COURSE FOR
ORANGE.
YOU GOTTA MOVE!
>> SHERRY, YOU GOTTA GO, BABY,
YOU GOTTA GO.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, BIG DIVE
INTO THE MUD.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO IT!
>> SHERRY, YOU GOTTA GO.
SHERRY, YOU GOTTA GO!
>> Jeff: SHERRY TAKING A LONG
TIME ON THE BALANCE BEAM, LONGER
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
GO, PURPLE!
PHILLIP, THE FIFTH AND FINAL
PERSON FOR PURPLE.
SHERRY COST HER TEAM A LOT OF
TIME ON THAT BALANCE BEAM.
ORANGE IS NOW ONE AND A HALF
PLAYERS BEHIND.
SHERRY HAS A BAG.
SHE'S HEADING THROUGH THE RICE.
PHILLIP NOW HEADING DOWN THE
SLIDE.
HE'S A BIG BOY.
IT'S A TIGHT FIT.
>>> ARRGGHHH!
>> Jeff: SHER STRUGGLING EVEN
THROUGH THE RICE.
GO, ORANGE!
BRENDA NOW ON THE COURSE FOR
ORANGE.
FIPIP HAS THE FIFTH AND FINAL
BAG FOR PURPLE.
START UNTYING, PURPLE.
BRENDA FLYING THROUGH THIS
COURSE.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THE BALLS, YOU
CAN START SHOOTING.
BRENDA THROUGH THE MUD, NOW
THROUGH THE RICE.
GO.
>> Jeff: PURPLE HAS ONE BALL
IN.
EDDIE, THE LAST PERSON ON THE
COURSE.
THERE'S THREE FOR PURPLE.
PURP WELTHEIR FOURTH BALL.
LET'S GO, EDDIE!
PURPLE WITH THEIR FIFTH BALL.
WITH THEIR SIXTH BALL.
THEIR SEVENTH BALL.
EDDIE THROUGH THE RICE.
ORANGE HAS A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE
UP.
PURP WELTHEIR TENTH.
BIG LEAD FOR PURPLE.
>> ONE MORE BALL.
>> Jeff: THEY CAN TASTE THAT
FOOD P.
>> BALL, BALL, BALL, BALL.
>> Jeff: PURPLE HAS ONE BALL
LEFT.
IT'S OVER!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: PURPLE WINS REWARD.
>> OH, YEAH!
AWESOME JOB.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, REYNOLD,
DAWN, ERIK, COCHRAN, PHILLIP,
NICE JOB.
NICE REWARD.
HAVE A GOOD AFTERNOON.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, BRENDA,
SHERRY, EDDIE, ANDREA, GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> HI, GUYS.
WELCOME.
WE HAVE PREPARED SOME FOOD AND
DRINKS FOR YOU.
TAKE A SHOWER, SIT BACK, RELAX,
AND ENJOY YOUR AFTERNOON.
>> THANK YOU!
>> FORGIVE US, WE'RE STARVING.
>> REYNOLD, DAWN, ERIK, PHILLIP
AND I WALKED INTO OUR REWARD
RESORT AND WE WERE GREETED BY A
TABLE FILLED TO THE BRIM WITH
ALL SORTS OF SHRIMP KABOBS, BEEF
KABOBS, FRIED CHICKEN, CALAMARI.
>> I HAVE NOT HAD ANY BEEF IN
WELL OVER A MONTH.
>> OH, GOODNESS.
PROTEIN IS IMPORTANT IN ONE'S
DIET, AND THIS IS THE SORT OF
ENERGY I NEED TO GO INTO
CHALLENGE AND TO CONTINUE TO BE
THE CHALLENGE MONSTER I THINK I
HAVE PROVEN MYSELF TO BE.
>> I REALIZED I HADN'T TURNED A
SHOWERHEAD ON IN 26 DAYS.
>> THERE'S SOAP!
>> JUST THE SMELL OF THE SOAP
WAS OVERPOWERING.
THIS MIGHT BE MY FAVORITE PART!
I NEEDED IT.
I'D BEEN LOSING MY MARBLES.
AND I THINK THE THING THAT'S
HARDEST FOR ME TO PROCESS ABOUT
THE GAME IS THAT IT MAKES YOU
FEEL KIND OF SCHIZOPHRENIC, HOW
QUICKLY THE EMOTIONS CHANGE.
>> OKAY, MUCH-NEEDED SHOWER.
>> THIS CLOUD JUST CAME OFF OF
YOU.
>> PHILLIP'S ETIQUETTE IS NOT
THE BEST.
THERE'S A SHOWER TO WASH OFF IN,
BUT PHILLIP DIVES INTO THE FOOD
AND GETS MUD AND RICE AND ALL
THIS HORRIBLE DIRTINESS INTO THE
POOL.
>> YOU'RE NAKED.
>> I'M NAKED?
>> THAT'S PRETTY MUCH WHAT
PHILLIP HAS DONE THE WHOLE
SEASON, JUST JUMPS IN WITHOUT
CARE FOR ANYBODY ELSE, DOES
THINGS ON HIS OWN.
I'M REALLY SICK OF PHILLIP BEING
AROUND.
>> I'M LOVING LIFE.
>> I'M EXHAUSTED.
I THINK I'VE PROBABLY SLEPT TWO
TO FOUR HOURS IN THE LAST THREE
DAYS.
MY BRAIN HAS NOT RESTED, SO I'VE
BECOME NERVOUS ABOUT HOW THE
NEXT STAGE OF THE GAME IS GOING
TO PLAY OUT.
I'M PARANOID ABOUT BEING
BLINDSIDED, YOU KNOW.
I IN THE SEVEN?
AND ARE THE PEOPLE I THINK HAVE
BEEN ALIGNED WITH ME REALLY
ALIGNED WITH ME?
ANDREA HAS BEEN SPENDING MOST OF
HER TIME WITH MALCOLM AND WITH
EDDIE.
I MEAN, SHE'S SO ASSIMILATED
WITH THEM.
AND IF EDDIE, REYNOLD, AND
MALCOLM WERE ABLE TO PULL
SOMEONE FROM OUR SEVEN OVER,
THEY COULD BLINDSIDE ME.
>> IF ANDREA FLIPS WITH MALCOLM
AND THEY SPLIT A VOTE, THEY NEED
FOUR TO TAKE ME OUT.
THEY HAVE FOUR.
SHE'S GOING TO DO IT.
>> LISTEN TO ME, ANDREA WOULD BE
ONE OF THE TARGETS.
YOU SCREW UP, YOU GO AGAINST THE
ALLIANCE, WE BOOT YOU OUT.
I SAY TO THEM, ANDREA WOULD IN
FACT BE THE FIRST TARGET BUT I
MIGHT BE LOOKING AT SOMEBODY
ELSE RIGHT NOW.
DAWN!
TRUE GRIT ABUSE SHE'S TOTALLY A
LUNATIC AND SHE'S LOSING HER
COMPOSURE OUT HERE.
ARE YOU NOT THE TARGET.
AND THE MOST IMPORTANT THING FOR
YOU TO DO IS ACT LIKE YOU
NORMALLY DO ON DAYS LIKE TODAY.
>> DAWN'S CONVINCED THAT ANDREA
IS GOING TO FLIP OVER AND VOTE
HER, DAWN, OUT.
HOW DAWN IS SO CONFIDENT SHE'S
THE PERSON THAT WOULD BE ON THE
RECEIVING END OF THIS VOTE IS
BAFFLING TO ME.
IT'S MAKING ME SUSPICIOUS OF
DAWN, QUITE FRANKLY.
>> CAN WE PUT THIS BACK ON?
>> YOU WANT MORE?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M A HAPPIER PERSON NOT
HUNGRY.
OR TIRED.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
IT'S SO HARD ON ME.
>> WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
I NEED A BREAK.
ALL I DID WAS TAKE A PIECE OF
COCONUT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE--
>> YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING?
>> I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
>> SHE'S OUT OF CONTROL.
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE'S LIVING IN A WORLD OF
TONIGHT PARANOIA.
>> SHE'S-- YEAH.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S THE
CLOSE QUARTERS.
>> THERE'S NO ESCAPE, YEAH.
>> I MEAN, HONESTLY FEEL LIKE
UNSTABLE.
>> IT'S OVERWHELMING.
>> I THINK I MIGHT NEED SOME
TIME JUST ALONE OR SOMETHING.
SORRY, COCHRAN.
I'M TOUGHER THAN THIS.
>> YOU'RE STILL BEING VERY
TOUGH.
JUST CRY OR WHATEVER.
>> I CRY MORE THAN A BABY.
LITERALLY.
>> WE HAD ONE WHO FLEW OVER THE
CUCKOO'S NEST, HANTZ, HE'S GONE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE'S ANOTHER
POSSIBLE HUMMING BIRD ZIPPING
OVER THE CUCKOO'S NEST, AND HER
NAME IS DAWN.
>> I'M SO TIRED OF CRYING.
>> I SLEPT.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> DID YOU STAY DRY?
>> YEAH I SLEPT THAT WHOLE
NIGHT.
>> NICE.
THAT'S GOOD.
>> YA.
TODAY IS DAY 28.
THE DAY I WENT HOME LAST TIME I
PLAYED, BUT AFTER ALL OF
YESTERDAY, AND MY, YOU KNOW,
MELTDOWN TORNADO, I WOKE UP
TODAY FEELING LIKE MYSELF.
I FEEL LIKE MY HEAD'S CLEAR, THE
GAME ISN'T OVERWHELMING ME.
I SLEPT.
I FEEL LIKE REBOOT.
THE GAME WAS OVERWHELMING ME.
AND I REALLY WASN'T IN CONTROL.
BUT TODAY I FEEL GOOD.
I FEEL GOOD ABOUT OUR ALLIANCE.
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE A QUICK
BRIEFING AS A GROUP.
I THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> TAKE A WALK?
>> OKAY.
>> NOW THAT DAUB SETTLED DOWN WE
WERE ON THE EVE OF ANOTHER
TRIBAL COUNCIL, STEALTH "R" US,
BEING LED BY PHILLIP, DECIDED IT
WOULD BE GOOD TO GET OUR DUCKS
IN A ROW AND SAY WHO ARE WE
REALLY VOTING OFF TONIGHT?
>> WHO DO YOU WANT?
>> I PROBABLY WANT REYNOLD OUT.
>> REYNOLD.
>> I WANT REYNOLD FIRST, BECAUSE
REQUEST CHALLENGE THAT GUY GOES
UP, HIS STRENGTH IS QUITE
PHENOMENAL.
I WANT HIM GONE FIRST.
>> TONIGHT, NOTHING CAN REALLY
GO WRONG.
>> OKAY.
>> AS LONG AS WE'RE ALL ON THE
SAME PAGE.
>> SO THE FOUR GIRLS ARE GOING
TO VOTE REYNOLDS.
>> WE HAVE SEVEN PEOPLE AGAINST
THEIR THREE.
WE'RE GOING TO SPLIT THE VOTE.
WE CAN THROW FOUR VOTES TO
REYNOLD, AND IN CASE SOMETHING
GOOFY HAPPENS WE'LL THROW THE
OTHER THREE TO MALCOLM AND FLUSH
OUT ANY POSSIBLE IDOLS.
I DON'T MEAN TO BE TOO CONFIDENT
BUT MY ALLIANCE HAS THE NUMBERS
AND I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER.
>> STEALTH!
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
BRENDA, TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
TODAY'S CHALLENGE WILL RUN IN
TWO HEAT.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL RACE ACROSS A
PLATFORM, JUMP IN TO THE OCEAN,
THEN SWIM BACK UNDER THE
PLATFORM BY PULLING YOURSELF
ALONG WITH THE ROPE.
YOU'LL CLIMB BACK ON TO THE
PLATFORM, GRAB A RING, AND MOVE
IT TO THE SECOND POST.
FIRST TWO PEOPLE FROM EACH HEAT
TO GET BOTH THEIR RINGS MOVE ON
TO THE FINAL ROUND.
THE WINNER OF THE FINAL ROUND
WINS IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE
IN WHAT, MALCOLM?
>> NINE!
>> Jeff: ONE IN NINE SHOT AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 28 DAYS,
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
THIS CHALLENGE IS GOING TO GO
QUICKLY, AND IT'S GOING TO
COMPLETELY EXHAUST YOU.
WHATEVER ENERGY YOU HAVE RIGHT
NOW, YOU NEED TO USE IT HERE.
BIELE DRAW FOR SPOTS AND GET
STARTED.
FIRST HEAT WE HAVE REYNOLD,
COCHRAN, DUNE, ANDREA, AND
SHERRY.
TWO PEOPLE WILL MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ANDREA NOT MESSING AROUND.
REYNOLD OFF TO A FAST START.
WHO'S GOING TO COME UP FIRST?
REYNOLD FLYING THROUGH THIS
COURSE.
DAWN RIGHT BEHIND HIM.
THERE'S ANDREA.
TWO PEOPLE ARE MOVING ON.
REYNOLD IN THE LEAD.
ANDREA RIGHT THERE.
DAWN BEHIND.
COCK EXPRAN SHERRY FALLING
BEHIND QUICKLY.
THERE'S REYNOLD.
HE'S GOT NO COMPETITION.
REYNOLD GOING TO MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND.
ONE SPOT LEFT.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
ANDREA HAS IT.
ANDREA MOVING ON TO THE FINAL
ROUND WITH REYNOLD!
ALL RIGHT, NEXT FIVE.
>> I'M SITTING OUT, JEFF.
I'M GOING TO SIT OUT THIS ONE.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP IS NOT GOING
TO PARTICIPATE.
>> NOPE, NOT GOING TO DO THIS
ONE.
>> HOW COME?
>> AS A BOY I HAD AN INCIDENT IN
THE WATER AND I JUST FEEL REALLY
UNCOMFORTABLE WITH THIS
PARTICULAR CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE YOU'LL BE
UNDERWATER SO LONG?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NEXT FOUR
HEAD OUT.
YOUR ODDS JUST INCREASED 20%
WITH IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
PHILLIP GOING TO SIT IT OUT.
28 DAYS INTO A GAME IN WHICH THE
ONLY THING THAT GIVES YOU
SECURITY IS IMMUNITY, THAT'S HOW
BIG THAT FEAR IS.
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: FOR THE SECOND HEAT,
IT IS BRENDA, MALCOLM, EDDIE,
AND ERIK, ONE SPOT IS VACANT,
PHILLIP IS NOTE GOING TO RUN.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST OUT OF THE WATER IS
MALCOLM, FOLLOWED BY EDDIE, AND
ERIK, AND BRENDA
EVERYBODY IN THIS.
THIS ROUND WILL DETERMINE IT.
IT IS MALCOLM, AND EDDIE.
MALCOLM GOING TO MOVE ON.
EDDIE-- NO, EDDIE DIDN'T GET HIS
RING ON!
THAT OPENS THE DOOR FOR BRENDA
AND ERIK.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
BRENDA GOING TO MOVE ON TO THE
FINAL ROUND WITH MALCOLM.
BIG ERROR BY EDDIE.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FINAL ROUND.
FIVE RINGS FOR THIS ROUND.
ONE WINNER.
SOMEBODY GOING TO BE WEARING
THIS NECKLACE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
THE OTHER NINE WILL BE
VULNERABLE.
REYNOLD, ANDREA, BRENDA, AND
MALCOLM, TWO MEN, TWO WOMEN,
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIVE RINGS IS GOING TO
COMPLETELY EXHAUST THEM.
MALCOLM AND REYNOLD UP FIRST,
SIDE BY SIDE, FOLLOWED BY ANDREA
AND BRENDA.
MALCOLM OFF TO A BIT OF A LEAD
OVER REYNOLD.
BUT IT IS A LONG CHALLENGE.
IT IS MALCOLM AND REYNOLD UP
TOGETHER AGAIN.
BOTH IN THE WATER TOGETHER.
ANDREA AND BRENDA STARTING TO
FALL BEHIND.
REYNOLD NOW IN THE LEAD.
MALCOLM RIGHT BEHIND.
IT IS NECK AND NECK BETWEEN
REYNOLD AND MALCOLM.
REYNOLD IS OUT OF THE WATER
FIRST.
MALCOLM NOW STRUGGLING.
REYNOLD WITH HIS FOURTH RING.
MALCOLM WITH HIS FOURTH RING,
ONE RING LEFT.
THIS IS IT!
RIGHT HERE!
WHO WILL POP OUT OF THE WATER
FIRST?
IT IS REYNOLD.
REYNOLD WINS IMMUNITY!
>> DID I DO IT!
>> YEAH, YOU DID IT!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY GAVE
EVERYTHING THEY HAD.
REYNOLD, YOU GOT ENOUGH ENERGY
TO SWIM OVER AND GET IMMUNITY?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: REYNOLD,
CONGRATULATIONS.
GOING INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL SAFE
TONIGHT, GUARANTEE AID ONE IN
NINE SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> ANYBODY ELSE DESTROYED?
>> ALL THESE PEOPLE ARE CUT
THROAT.
THEY WANT ME OUT, I'M THE
BIGGEST THREAT.
I HAVE THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE,
I'M GOING TO DO WHATEVER I WANT.
>> NICE JOB, REYNOLD.
>> I HAVE RESPECT FOR ALL OF
YOU.
>> I HAVE NO RESPECT FOR
PHILLIP.
I MEAN, WHEN WHATWHEN IT BOILS
DOWN TO IT, HE'S ALL TALK.
HE'S NO ACTION.
I THINK IT'S SACK RELIGIOUS NOT
TO PARTICIPATE IN AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, ESPECIALLY AND I HAVE
LIONS AND GORILLAS TATTOOED ON
YOUR BODY.
COME ON, MAN.
>> I WANTED TO SPEAK TO YOU FOR
A SECOND, IF I COULD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
UPON.
>> WE'RE GONNA STILL SPLIT?
>> OKAY.
>> I'M FINALLY IN THE LEADERSHIP
POSITION.
I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT JUST
MIGHT HAVE A SHOT OF GETTING TO
THE FINAL THREE.
AND IF THESE PEOPLE AREN'T
BITTER, I MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE A
SHOT OF WINNING.
>> HERE'S MY PLAN SO THAT YOU
KNOW.
WE'RE GONNA SPLIT THE VOTES.
ONE OF THE BEAUTEZ OF BEING
NUMBERS OF 7-3, IS THAT IT
DOESN'T MATTER.
MALCOLM CAN HAVE AN IDOL, AND IT
WOULD BE FOUR MALCOLM, THREE
EDDIE.
SO ONE OF THOSE TWO ARE GOING TO
GO HOME.
MALCOLM DISTRIBUTE HAVE AN IDOL.
SO HE'S SITTING THERE
( WHISTLING )
AND BYE-BYE.
>> MY HEAD IN THE GUILLOTINE
RIGHT NOW, BUT THE IDEA NOW IS I
HAVE THE IDOL.
NO MATTER WHAT.
I PLAY THAT THING, I'M NOT GOING
HOME.
BUT THE IDEA IS TO GET THROUGH
THIS VOTE AND STILL HAVE THE
IDOL.
I HAVE A FEELING THAT WE'VE JUST
MISSED.
>> I'M ALL FOR LOOKING FOR
IDOLS, DUDE.
>> I'M CONVINCED IT'S ON THIS
PATH.
>> HERE?
>> YEAH.
THE POSSIBILITY STILL EXISTS
THERE'S ANOTHE IDOL ON THE OUT
THERE AND I HAVE A FEW HOURS,
AND NOTHING ELSE TO DO, AND NO
ONE ELSE HAS ASKED, SO MAYBE
THIS DREAM WILL COME TRUE.
>> I GOT TRAPPED ONCE AS A BOY.
I WAS AT A POND.
AND THEY HAD ONE OF THOSE
THINGS-- SO I THINK-- I THINK
THE HOTTEST PLACE FOR THE IDOL
IS THE INTROONS TO THE WATER.
>> GRAY.
>> AFTER THE CHALLENGE, ANDREA
IS LIKE LET'S LOOK FOR THE IDOL
AND I SAY ABSOLUTELY.
BECAUSE IT'S TIME TO WORK,
PEOPLE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE SIT
AROUND SO MUCH AT CAMP.
THERE'S A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> SO IT WAS, LIKE... LIKE, NOT
FUN.
>> YEAH, I DON'T WANT TO DO
THAT.
>> THIS STUPID THING COULD BE
ANYWHERE.
>> I MEAN, IT'S A NEED UNTIL A
HAYSTACK.
JUST LET ME KNOW IF IT'S BACK
THERE.
I WILL COME HELP.
>> I WILL NOT BE ABLE TO CONTAIN
MYSELF.
>> WOULD IT BE TOO MUCH FOR A
CLUE?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
>> WHAT?
>> YOU SAID THAT.
>> YOU JUST FOUND IT.
>> YOU JUST SAID THAT AND I SAW
IT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU HAD IT HIDDEN.
>> I SWEAR TO GOD I JUST SAW IT.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN MALCOLM REACH
INTIEZ ROARKE FINDS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITYITE IDOL RIGHT IN FRONT
OF US.
>> MALCOLM, WAY TO GO.
GOOD FOR YOU.
>> MALCOLM WAS SUPPOSED TO GO
HOME, BUT HE FOUND THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL EXACTLY WHEN HE
NEEDED TO FIND IT.
SO EDDIE HAS TO GO NOW.
MALCOLM JUT FOUND THE IDOL.
>> IN FRONT OF YOU?
>> YEAH, WE WERE RIGHT BY HIM.
>> HAD HIM OPEN IT IN FRONT OF
US.
>> SAME PLAN.
MAYBE HE WON'T PLAY IT.
LET'S NOT GET FANCY.
IF HE PLAYS IT, WHICH I ASSUME
HE WILL, THERE'S GOING TO BE A
REVOTE.
>> PERFECT.
>>Y KNOW HE HAS IT.
EVERYONE JUST ACT NORMAL.
>> HE SHOWED IT TO YOU?
>> YEAH, WE SAW IT.
>> WHO CARES.
>> OKAY.
>> WE GOT THE NUMBERS.
>> SO MALCOLM IS PROTECTED
TONIGHT.
AND REYNOLD WON IMMUNITY.
NOW I'M DOUBLE SCREWED BECAUSE
MY ONLY CHANCE FOR STAYING
ANOTHER DAY WAS IF THEY DECIDED
TO VOTE OFF MALCOLM INSTEAD OF
ME.
ASK NOW THE ENTIRE CAMP KNOWS HE
HAS THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I'M GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
MICHAEL, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO BASED ON THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, REYNOLD, IT WOULD SEEM
THAT YOU, EDDIE, AND MALCOLM ARE
STILL ON THE OUTS.
>> DEFINITELY AGREE WITH THAT,
YEAH.
SO FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, I FELT
LIKE IT WAS PRETTY MUCH WIN
IMMUNITY OR YOU'RE GOING HOME
TONIGHT SCENARIO.
>> Jeff: EDDIE, WOULD YOU
AGREE WITH THAT?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, ONE OF THE
THREE OF US IS GOING TO NEED TO
WIN IT EVERY TIME IN ORDER TO
KEEP GOING.
BUT YOU TRY TO TAKE ALL THE
POSITIVE YOU CAN FROM THE WHOLE
EXPERIENCE, YOU KNOW.
EVERYTHING I'VE DONE I'LL
REMEMBER FOREVER.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, EDDIE IS
TALKING LIKE HE'S GONE.
>> IT'S VERY TRUE.
EVERYONE IS LOOKING AT EDDIE,
BECAUSE MALCOLM HAPPENED UPON
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> Jeff: SO EVERYONE KNOWS YOU
HAVE AN IDOL.
>> WE WERE RIGHT THERE.
>> YEAH.
>> DAWN AND I WERE WALKING, AND
MALCOLM TURNS AROUND AND FINDS
IT IN A ROCK.
SO HE--
>> PRETTY STOKED.
>> REYNOLD WON WHEN HE NEEDED
TO, AND HE FOUND HIS IDOL WHEN
HE NEEDED TO.
>> Jeff: SO THAT, COCHRAN, WHY
THE TARGET IS ON EDDIE.
>> I DON'T THINK HE WAS
ANYBODY'S FIRST CHOICE.
>> Jeff: WHO WAS THE FIRST
CHOICE?
>> PROBABLY REYNOLD.
HE'S THE SORT OF GUY WHO CAN
CHARM HIS WAY TO THE TOP.
HE WON IMMUNITY SO I THINK
EVERYBODY VIEWS HIM AS A HUGE,
HUGE THREAT.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU
MADE HISTORY.
I CAN'T THINK OF A TIME SOMEONE
HAS VOLUNTEERED TO STAY OUT OF A
CHALLENGE WHEN NOT TEMPTED BY
FOOD.
>> WHEN I WAS A SMALL BOY, I
WENT SWIMMING WITH A GROUP OF
KIDS AND I GOT TRAPPED UNDER THE
DECK.
I GOT DISORIENTED, AND
FORTUNATELY FOR ME THE OWNER
FOUND ME AND PULLED ME UP OUT OF
THE WATER.
THAT'S SOMETHING I'VE ALWAYS
BEEN FEARFUL OF.
FOR ME, THAT IS THE DECISION I
WOULD HAVE MADE AGAIN AND AGAIN.
>> Jeff: FAIR ENOUGH.
ANDREA, HOW IS CAMP LIFE?
>> YOU KNOW, THERE'S A LOT OF
PARANOIA, TO THE POINT WHERE WE
DON'T TALK TO REYNOLDS, EDDIE,
AND MALCOLM, WHICH IS REALLY
STRESSFUL BECAUSE I WAS ON GOTA
WITH THEM AND REALLY ENJOYED
THEIR COMPANY BUT IT MADE A LOT
OF PEOPLE PARANOID ABOUT ME AND
I THINK I WAS EVEN A TARGET AT
ONE POINT.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, IS THERE
TENSION?
>> YEAH, MYSELF, EDDIE, AND
REYNOLD ARE ON THE OUTS.
WE'RE KIND OF LIKE WE HAVE THE
PLAGUE OR SOMETHING.
BUT THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE A
GAME, SO WE FIGURED WE'D DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT, AND TONIGHT
WE'RE GOING TO TRY.
THIS IS THE OTHER IMMUNITY IDOL
I'VE BEEN HANGING ON TO, I'M
GIVING IT TO EDDIE.
YEAH, I HAD THAT ONE FOR A
WHILE.
I JUST FOUND THE OTHER ONE
TODAY.
>> Jeff: SO JUST TO BE CLEAR
HOLD TIGHT.
THE LOOKS ON FACES.
ANDREA CAN'T EVEN LOOK UP.
MALCOLM, THIS IS RARE WHEN
TRIBAL GETS THIS CRAZY.
ARE YOU AWARE THAT DAWN AND
BRENDA ARE TALKING.
COCHRAN AND ERIK ARE WHISPERING.
ANDREA HAS HER HAND IF HER FACE.
WHAT A SHIFT.
>> THAT WAS THE IDEA.
THAT WAS--
( LAUGHTER )
PEOPLE ARE STILL WHISPERING.
THERE MUST BE PARANOIA RIGHT NOW
FROM EVERYONE GOING ARE THEY
SAYING MY NAME?
>> EXCEPT THE THREE AMIGOS.
FOR ONCE.
>> Jeff: SO, MALCOLM, I KEEP
INTERRUPTING YOU--
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> Jeff: THEY'RE STILL
TALKING.
I FEEL LIKE I WANT AN INDIVIDUAL
PAUSE BUTTON AND WANT TO HIT
PAUSE FOR THE OTHER NINE.
>> I KNOW FOR ONE VOTE WE HAVE
CONTROL.
ONE OF THE SEVEN OF THIS VERY
TIGHT GROUP ARE GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: DAWN, YOU WERE IN
CONTROL OF THIS GAME LIKE 20
SUCCESS OKAY.
>> HONESTLY, I'M THE FAINTINGY
SHEEP IN THIS GAME, PEOPLE
SAYING THINGS AND I GO, BOOM, IS
IT AND FALL OVER.
EVERY DAY THE GAME CHANGES FOR
ME.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, YOU WERE
SAYING?
>> WHERE WAS?
OH, YEAH, WE'RE GOING HOME.
WE'RE GOING TO BE SAFE TONIGHT
BUT TOMORROW MORNING THE
SITUATION HAS NOT REALLY
CHANGED.
WE'RE GOING TO BE DOWN 6-3.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT, BUT WE'LL
THROW IT OUT THERE, THE THREE OF
US ARE VOTING FOR PHILLIP.
I DON'T NEED TO GO DOWN A LIST
OF REASONES YES.
EVERYONE KNOWS IN THEIR HEADS.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE A GAME,
AND IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE FUN.
BUT IT'S NOT FUN ANYMORE I CAME
OUT HERE TO HAVE THE TIME OF MY
LIFE.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE SAYING FILL
IEP.
>> PHILLIP IS THE FUN SPONGE.
HE SUCKS IT ALL OUT OF THE
GROUP.
IT'S A GAME BUT IT DOESN'T HAVE
TO BE A MILITARISTIC THING WHERE
WE'RE ALL IN BASIC TRAINING.
>> THAT IS NOT HOW I PLAY THE
GAME.
HE IS TRYING TO LABEL ME AS
SOMETHING I'M NOT.
>> Jeff: WOW, SO, WHERE ARE
WE?
ANDREA, I'M GUESSING YOUR BEST
BET RIGHT NOW IS TO SAY, SURE,
PHILLIP, ABSOLUTELY PHILLIP.
I KNOW MAO TO SPELL IT, TWO
"Ls" AND WOON "P."
>> IT'S TRUE, HE HAS A THE LOVE
CONSERVATION AT ONCE.
I WAS ONCE A TARGET SO, I'M
STILL VERY PARANOID.
>> Jeff: IS THAT A BIG PART OF
THIS, ANDREA?
WHAT IS IT THIS IS A DOUBLE PLAY
AND THIS IS NOT WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN?
>> EXACTLY.
I MEAN, I'M VERY SCARED.
>> I CAN SAY SOMETHING?
>> Jeff: YEAH.
>> YES, ALL THREE OF THEM ARE
LIKE, WE'RE THE THREE AMIGOS,
THESE ARE OUR IDOLS, WE'RE GOING
TO PLAY THEM.
BUT THERE IS SOME BONUS IN
KEEPING ONE IDOL.
IF ONE PERSON DECIDES NOT TO
PLAY IT.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, YET A NEW
WRINKLE.
THE FACT THAT THEY'RE WEARING
THEM MEANS NOTHING.
THEY NEED TO GIVE THEM TO US.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD VOTE THE
WAY WE SAID WE WOULD VOTE WHEN
WE CAME IN HERE.
FIHAVE TO GO HOME, I HAVE TO GO
HOME.
BUT I'D RATHER DO IT
STRATEGICALLY THAN MALIGN MY
CHARACTER.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, YOU HAVE
WRITTEN PAPERS ABOUT SURVIVOR
>> I'M HAVING A BIPOLAR
REACTION.
BECAUSE THE "SURVIVOR" FAN IS
SITTING HOME SAYING THIS IS THE
MOST EXCITING FREAKING TRIBAL
COUNCIL I HAVE EVER SEEN.
PEOPLE ARE WHISPERING, AND
VOTING IS CHANGE CHICAGO IS
EXTREMELY RARE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
SO THIS IS GOING TO BE A GAMBLE.
>> Jeff: WHAT IS IT IT IS
ABOUT TAKING OUT ONE OF THE
OTHER SIX AND THEY'RE SHOVING
EVERYTHING TOWARDS PHILLIPS IS A
MISDIRECT.
>> I THINK IT JUST TAKES A
COUPLE US TO VOTE AND TAKE
SOMEONE OUT THAT'S IN THE
ALLIANCE THAT'S NOT PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: SO THE QUESTIONS AS
WE GO TO THE VOTE ARE WHO ARE
THE THREE AMIGOS GOING TO VOTE
FOR?
WHO ARE THE SEVEN GOING TO VOTE
AND ARE EDDIE AND MALCOLM GOING
TO PLAY THEIR INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY IDOLS?
ALL RIGHT, ONE OF THE CRAZIEST
TRIBALS EVER.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
PHILLIP, YOU'RE UP.
>> WHATEVER HAPPENS TONIGHT,
THIS IS WHY I FREAKING LOVE
"SURVIVOR" AND HAVE FOR 13
YEARS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
>> Jeff: EDDIE AND MALCOLM
BOTH PLAYED THEIR IDOLS.
ANY VOTE CAST FOR EDDIEO MALCOLM
WILL NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MALCOLM.
DOES NOT COUNT.
MALCOLM.
EDDIE.
DOES NOT COUNT.
PHILLIP.
ONE VOTE PHILLIP.
TWO VOTES PHILLIP.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
PHILLIP.
THAT'S THREE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
PHILLIP, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: WELL, IN ONE OF THE
CRAZIEST TRIBALS EVER, REYNOLD,
EDDIE, AND MALCOLM SURVIVE
ANOTHER VOTE.
THE QUESTION IS DID THEY CHANGE
THE GAME ENOUGH TO SURVIVE
ANOTHER VOTE?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, EDDIE, AND
MALCOLM LOOK TO RECRUIT NEW
ALLIES.
>> YOU CAN'T BEAT THEM, YOU JOIN
THEM.
>> Jeff: WHEN WHO DOESN'T LOVE
"SURVIVOR" AUCTION?
HOW OFTEN DOES THAT HAPPEN?
>> MORE OFTEN THAN YOU THINK.
>> I FEEL I PLAYED A GREAT GAME.
I AM SO HAPPY WITH THE WAY I
PLAYED.
I TRIED TO BRING INTO THE GAME
SOME THINGS I LEARNED FROM
BOSTON ROB.
I FELT OFTEN LIKE I CAN IN
"SURVIVOR" SEASON 22.
I WASN'T RESPECTED.
I WASN'T APPRECIATED FOR THE
THINGS THAT I DO.
THAT PART HURTS FOR ME.
I'M FEELING GOOD.
I, I PLAYED A GREAT GAME.
I KNOW I DID A VERY GOOD JOB OUT
HERE AND DID MY BEST.