>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
FROM DAY ONE EDDIE AND REYNOLD
HAVE BEEN FIGHTING TO STAY ALIVE
IN THE GAME.
>> TIGHT SPOT NOW FRIEND-O.
(LAUGHS).
>> Jeff: THEIR COUPLES
ALLIANCE WAS DECIMATED AND THE
ONLY THINGS KEEPING THEM ALIVE
WERE REYNOLDS' LUCK AT FINDING
IDOLS.
>> I MIGHT AS WELL JUST KEEP
PLAYING THEM IF I CAN JUST KEEP
FINDING THEM.
(LAUGHS)
>> Jeff: AND THEIR MUSCLES.
REYNOLD HASN'T MISSED YET, HE'S
ON FIRE.
DESPITE THE FANS KEEPING THEM
AROUND FOR THEIR STRENGTH IN
CHALLENGES, THEIR LOSING STREAK
CONTINUES.
MICHAEL RELEASES FOR THE FANS!
FAVORITES WIN REWARD!
AT THE FAVORITES CAMP, THE
STEALTH "R" US ALLIANCE HAD
THEIR SIGHTS SET ON ONE OF THEIR
OWN MEMBERS.
WHY ARE THEY LIKE INTENSELY
TALKING.
>> SHE IS IN THE CORE SIX BUT I
REALLY WANT CORRINE OUT.
>> Jeff: UNTIL BRANDON HAD A
BREAKDOWN, DESTROYING THEIR
CAMP.
>> HERE'S THE REASON TO VOTE ME
OUT YOU LITTLE -- HUH?
>> FORFEIT THE CHALLENGE?
GIVE IMMUNITY AWAY?
YOU NEVER DO THAT IN THIS GAME.
>> I'M THE AUTHOR OF MY FATE.
NOW VOTE ME OUT, BITCH!
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, THE FAVORITES' DESIRE
TO FORFEIT LED TO AN IMPROMPTU
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WE ARE GOING TO FORFEIT THE
CHALLENGE THAT WE MAY GO TO
TRIBAL.
>> THAT'S BULL (BLEEP)
CORRINE, COMPLETE BULL (BLEEP).
>> Jeff: BUT HE WOULDN'T GO
DOWN WITHOUT A FIGHT.
>> I'M TIRED OF YOU TALKING --
>> DON'T WALK THIS WAY.
>> I'LL COME OVER THERE AND
KNOCK YOUR (BLEEP)ING HEAD OFF.
I'M TELLING YOU.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, BRANDON
WAS VOTED OUT UNANIMOUSLY.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME, BRANDON.
>> GOOD LUCK.
KICK THEIR ASS.
>> Jeff: WELL, GAME JUST GOT A
LITTLE MORE INTERESTING.
14 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> WELL, OUR FIRST UNANIMOUS
VOTE, WE'RE UNITED.
>> HE GOT WHAT HE WANTED.
>> IT'S JUST GOING TO MAKE THEM
STRENGTH IN THEIR OWN HEAD THAT
THEY'LL PULL IT OFF.
>> I DON'T RESPECT ONE OUNCE OF
WHAT HE DID.
WE WOULD CALL THAT A TRAITOR.
>> HE GAVE THEM A HOPE AND A PEP
TALK.
>> HE DID SEVERE DAMAGE TO
MYSELF.
>> I FEEL THE SAME WAY ABOUT
>> ACTUALLY, I DIDN'T MIND HIM.
I HAD NO IDEA HE HATED ME.
>> HE WAS VERY HARD, HE WAS VERY
CRUEL, HE WAS VERY MEAN.
MEAN IN WHAT HE HAD TO SAY ABOUT
ALL OF US.
>> IT'S FINE THAT HE HATES ME
AND PHILLIP, BUT HE DID IT TO
YOU, HE LIKES YOU.
HE SPILLED YOUR RICE AND BEANS,
TOO.
HE'S SUCH A GOOD BUY GUYS, WE'RE
ALL BAD PEOPLE.
YOU JUST (BLEEP)ED THE SIX
REMAINING MEMBERS OF THE TRIBE
YOU LIKED.
>> HE EXAGGERATED.
I'M SURE THEY SIT AROUND AND SAY
THINGS ABOUT US AND IT'S NOT
LIKE WE'RE DOING THIS MEANING
HARM ON THIS THEM.
>> HE JUST WANTED TO GO DOWN
PLAYING.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE I EVER HAD
ONE CROSS WORD WITH HIM.
YOU NEVER SAW HIM AND I ARGUE,
LIKE HEY, MAN, YOU GO GET THE
WOOD, YOU GO DO THAT.
WE NEVER HAD IT.
IT WAS FALL THAT KID'S HEAD.
ALL OF IT.
I FEEL SORRY FOR BRANDON AND LET
ME TELL YOU, WHAT WAS GOING ON
WITH THAT GUY, IT TAKES A
PROFESSIONAL.
EVEN A SPECIALIST WOULDN'T TELL
YOU WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HIM.
>> I HOPE HE CAN NEVER PLAY THIS
GAME AGAIN BECAUSE QUITTERS
DON'T GET TO PLAY AGAIN.
HE IS OUT OF HIS MIND UP THERE
WITH MEL GIBSON AND ANY OTHER
CRAZY PERSON.
>> I'M SORRY YOU GOT CALLED OUT.
I'M SORRY YOU GOT CALLED OUT.
I WANTED TO SAY SOMETHING .
>> I WISH SOMEBODY WOULD HAVE
SAID THAT'S NOT WHO PHILLIP IS
OUT HERE.
I'M PISSED ABOUT IT.
>> IT DIDN'T NEED TO GO DOWN
LIKE THAT.
>> I DIDN'T CARE FOR THE FACT
THAT NOBODY JUMPED IN TO SAVE
PHILLIP OR I.
JOHN HAD SEVERAL OPPORTUNITIES
WHERE HE SAID WE LIKE THESE
PEOPLE, WE DON'T LIKE HIM.
>> IT'S UNFORTUNATE, BUT FRANKLY
WE'RE THE BETTER TRIBE.
WE'RE GOING TO WIN THIS THING,
ONE OF US IS GOING TO WIN THIS
THING.
WE HAVE TO REGROUP AND LET
BRANDON BE WHAT HE WAS AND MOVE
ON.
>> IT FEELS GOOD THAT HE'S GONE.
>> ABSOLUTELY TRUE.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE ON THAT.
ONE OF US WILL WIN THIS THING.
>> WHEN BRANDON WAS THERE IT WAS
LIKE A CERTIFIED ASYLUM.
IT'S COMFORTING TO KNOW BRANDON
WAS ABLE TO FLY OUT OF THE COO
COO'S NEST AND WE'RE LEFT WITH
PHILLIP.
>> WE'RE OUTGUNNED.
I EVALUATED.
WHEN I WAS LOOKING AT THEM, I
WAS TAKING THEM ALL IN, THE MEN
IN PARTICULAR.
THEY'RE WORN, THEY'RE BEATEN.
WE LOOK HEALTHY.
WE'RE GOING TO STAY HEALTHY.
BRANDON'S GONE, I'M ALREADY DONE
WITH HIM.
>> I HAD AN OPERATION CALLED
OPERATION THUNDER BALL, ALL OF
US WAS ON BOARD WITH IT TO GO
AFTER CORRINE.
SHE'S EGO DRIVEN AND GOING TO DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR HER.
THE FIRST OPPORTUNITY THAT I
HAVE TO TAKE A STILETTO AND GET
HER OUT OF THE GAME, SHE'S GONE.
>> WHAT'S IT SAY?
>> "BEATEN BY EXHAUSTION,
BATTERED BY THE WEATHER, WINNERS
WILL HAVE FUN AND CELEBRATE
TOGETHER."
>> LOSERS WILL BE DEPRESSED, GO
HOME TO A WET CAMP.
(LAUGHTER)
>> IT'S OVER FOR EDDIE AND I AS
FAR AS MAKING ANY KIND OF SOCIAL
ALLIANCES WITH ANYBODY HERE SO
I'M JUST GOING TO GO OUT, WIN
CHALLENGES, EAT RICE AND
HOPEFULLY SURVIVE LONG ENOUGH
THAT SOMETHING SHIFTS IN THE
GAME.
BECAUSE NOTHING IS SHIFTING IN
THIS CAMP.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
LAST TIME WE WERE TOGETHER IT
WAS PRETTY EMOTIONAL WITH
BRANDON LEAVING THE GAME.
MICHAEL, WHAT HAPPENS TO THE
TRIBE DYNAMIC WHEN SOMETHING
LIKE THAT GOES DOWN WITH BRANDON
ON THE FAVORITE TRIBE.
HOW DOES IT HELP YOU GUYS COME
TOGETHER?
>> WELL, IT WAS GOOD YESTERDAY
FOR US TO FEEL SOMETHING GOOD
TOGETHER INSTEAD OF FEELING THE
RAIN AND THE HUNGER AND THE
DAMPNESS.
IT WAS GOOD TO FEEL SOMETHING
POSITIVE TOGETHER AND TALK ABOUT
EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: MATT, DID THAT DO
ANYTHING TO CHANGE MOMENTUM
WITHIN THIS GROUP OF SIX?
>> YEAH, WE'VE DEFINITELY BEEN
BUMMED OUT LOSING SO MANY
CHALLENGES AND WE ALWAYS SAY OH,
IT WAS SO CLOSE" AND THIS AND
THAT.
BUT THE GOOD THING IS WE WERE
THINKING THAT, YOU KNOW, THE
FAVORITES HAD ALL THIS COMFORT
AND FULL BELLIES AND THIS AND
THAT AND WE THOUGHT THEIR CAMP
MIGHT HAVE BEEN THIS PERFECT
LITTLE FAMILY AND THEY OBVIOUSLY
WERE NOT ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY.
AND I ACTUALLY FEEL BAD FOR
PHILLIP.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES PHILLIP
APPEARS TO BE CRAZY AND THIS
WILD GUY BUT I WOULDN'T WANT
ANYONE TO -- YOU KNOW, SPILLING
THE BEANS AND RICE, THAT'S OVER
THE TOP AND TRUE CRAZINESS SO I
ACTUALLY FEEL BAD FOR YOU GUYS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, WHAT DO YOU
NOTICE DIFFERENT AROUND CAMP
OTHER THAN BRANDON'S PHYSICAL
PRESENCE BEING GONE?
>> IT WAS JUST HARMONY.
SO RELAXING.
WE HAD A REGULAR NIGHT'S SLEEP.
IN 36 HOURS I HADN'T SLEPT.
I HAD ONE EYE OPEN ALWAYS
LOOKING AT BRANDON WONDERING
WHAT THE HECK WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: SO 14 DAYS INTO THIS
GAME, BOTH TRIBES STILL VERY
GOOD ABOUT THE UNITY THAT YOU
HAVE RIGHT NOW.
GOOD, BECAUSE IT'S ABOUT TO
CHANGE AGAIN.
DROP YOUR BUFFS, WE ARE
SWITCHING TRIBES.
>> OH, MAN!
>> JEFF, YOU'RE KILLING ME!
I'M GOING TO GIVE EACH OF YOU AN
EGG AND ALL TOGETHER SMASH IT ON
YOUR CHEST, YOUR FACE, SOMEWHERE
ON YOUR BODY.
THE COLOR THAT COMES OUT OF THE
EGG WILL TELL YOU WHAT TRIBE YOU
WERE ON.
EVERYBODY READY?
THREE, TWO, ONE, SMASH.
OH!
>> Jeff: IF YOU WERE ORANGE,
TAKE A SPOT ON THE ORANGE MAT,
IF YOU'RE PURPLE TAKE A SPOT ON
THE PURPLE MAT.
>> HI, GUYS!
>> HI!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THE NEW
GOTA TRIBE IS EDDIE, REYNOLD,
ANDREA, MALCOLM, SHERRY, ERIC
AND BRENDA.
HERE ARE YOUR BUFFS.
THE NEW PURPLE TRIBE, CORRINE,
PHILLIP, MICHAEL, MATT, COCHRAN,
JULIA AND DAWN, YOU ARE BIG CAL.
PUT ON YOUR BUFFS.
BIKAL.
COCHRAN, YOU'RE A STUDENT OF THE
GAME.
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> THE GAME JUST STARTED ANEW.
>> Jeff: MATT, HOW ARE YOU
DOING?
THE GUY YOU WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT FEELING SORRY FOR,
PHILLIP, IS NOW YOUR TRIBE MATE.
>> I KNOW, I'M ACTUALLY REAL
PSYCHED TO BE ON THIS TRIBE.
I ACTUALLY LIKE ALL THESE
PLAYERS.
WHAT CAN YOU DO, YOU KNOW?
LIKE MOVE ON.
I'M PSYCHED TO SWITCH THINGS UP
A BIT.
>> Jeff: CORRINE, HOW ARE YOU
FEELING?
YOU WERE ON THE FAVORITE TRIBE,
YOU WERE DOMINATING AND NOW
EVERYTHING'S DIFFERENT.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, IT'S DEFINITELY
AN ADJUSTMENT.
I'M A LITTLE BIT --
>> Jeff: WERE YOU ABOUT TO SAY
INJUSTICE?
>> NO, I'M JUST OVERWHELMED.
YOU'RE SORT OF LIKE -- I'VE NOT
SAID BASICALLY TWO WORDS TO THE
OTHER TRIBE THIS WHOLE TIME SO
IT'S LIKE GETTING TO KNOW THEM.
MEETING NEW PEOPLE IS NICE.
I GET TO STAY ON MY CAMP.
I DON'T KNOW, I'M VERY
OVERWHELMED.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, ASSESS THESE
TWO NEW TRIBES.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE STRONG.
I'M JUST LOOKING AT IT, IT LOOKS
LIKE WE HAVE A STRONG TEAM.
>> Jeff: SO YOU WOULD GIVE THE
ADVANTAGE TO YOUR TRIBE?
STRENGTH WISE?
>> IN A SITUATION LIKE THIS I
CAN SAY I'M PRETTY HAPPY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELL GOOD
NEWS ON THE FOOD FRONT.
YOU EACH HAVE ANOTHER BAG OF
RICE TO REPLENISH.
>> WE ARE GOING TO NEED THAT.
>> Jeff: YOU ALSO HAVE A NEW
FLINT IN CASE THE ONE YOU HAVE
IS WEARING OUT.
GOTA, BIKAL, GRAB YOUR STUFF AND
HEAD TO YOUR NEW HOME, THIS GAME
JUST STARTED OVER.
>> I COULD NOT BE HAPPIER ABOUT
THIS NEW TRIBE.
I WAS THIS CLOSE TO BREAKING AND
NOW IT'S LIKE A WHOLE NEW LIFE,
WHOLE NEW CHANCE, WHOLE NEW
GAME.
DAY ONE FOR EDDIE AND ME NOW.
>> THANK YOU!
>> WELL, IT WORKED OUT WELL FOR
US.
THIS IS ALL RIGHT WITH ME.
>> I DON'T WANT TO JINX US BUT I
DON'T THINK WE SHOULD MOVE IN
ANY SCENARIO.
>> AS FAR AS CHALLENGES ARE
CONCERNED, I DON'T SEE THEM
BEATING US IN ANYTHING.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE WE'RE THE
GODS.
>> I'M ECSTATIC.
I THINK THE GOTA TRIBE IS THE
BEST THAT IT COULD POSSIBLY BE
RIGHT NOW.
WE ARE THE YOUNG GOOD LUCKING
TRIBE.
IT'S AWESOME.
>> GROUP HUG!
THEORETICALLY THE FAVORITE CANS
DO WHATEVER THEY WANT BECAUSE
THERE'S FOUR OF THEM AND THREE
OF THE FANS BUT I DON'T THINK
WE'RE GOING TO GO TO A TRIBAL
COUNCIL FOR A LITTLE BIT SO I
THINK MY CHANCES OF GOING
FURTHER IN THIS GAME
SIGNIFICANTLY INCREASED.
AND SO THE STORY YOU GUYS DON'T
HAVE IS EDDIE AND I ARE THE ONES
EVEN KEEPING US IN THESE
CHALLENGES, THEY'VE BEEN TRYING
TO VOTE US OUT SINCE DAY TWO.
>> WHO HAS?
>> SHERRI.
SHE'S THE WORST.
SHE WAS IN LINE WITH EVERYBODY
ELSE BUT ME AND HIM.
>> WE ARE TOTALLY ON OUR OWN SO
IF YOU WANT TO VOTE HER OUT,
WE'RE WITH YOU.
>> YEAH, WE DON'T CARE.
>> RIGHT AWAY, AS SOON AS WE HIT
THE BEACH, REYNOLD AND EDDIE
PITCHED ME AND MALCOLM THIS IDEA
THAT SHERRY IS ON THE OUTSIDE
AND SHE'S THE PERSON WE NEED TO
GET OFF THE ISLAND SO THAT-TO-ME
THAT RAISES RED FLAGS.
I LOOK AT REYNOLD AND I THINK
USED CAR SALESMAN.
HE'S GOT BEAUTIFUL BABY BLUE
EYES TALKING THE TALK BUT IT'S
NOT ALL IT SEEMS.
>> SHERRI'S OVER THERE TRYING TO
MAKE A NEW ALLIANCE.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT'S EDDIE LIKE?
IS HE A --
>> EDDIE IS A WONDERFUL GUY WHEN
HE'S NOT WITH REYNOLD AND HE'S
THE BIGGEST SALESMAN, REYNOLD.
>> SO IF WE LOSE WHO DO YOU WANT
TO GO?
>> WHO DO YOU THINK?
(LAUGHTER)
>> HE WOULDN'T TELL YOU IF HE
FOUND AN IDOL, RIGHT?
>> REYNOLD PLAYED HIS IMMUNITY
IDOL AT TRIBAL COUNCIL BUT I
THINK HE'S OUT LOOKING FOR IT
CONSTANTLY.
>> SHERRI SPILLED THE BEANS OF
THE WHOLE TRIBE TO BRENDA AND I
ABOUT REYNOLD AND EDDIE.
SHE KIND OF SPOILED EVERYTHING
ABOUT THEIR TRIBE WHICH IS GOOD
NEWS FOR US BECAUSE WE'RE STILL
THINKING ALONG THE LINES OF
FAVORITES VERSUS FANS.
WE OBVIOUSLY YOU APPRECIATE YOU
TELLING US THIS INFORMATION.
>> HERE WE ARE!
>> HOME SWEET HOME.
>> LET'S SHOW YOU WHERE
EVERYTHING IS.
>> NEW TRIBE IS ME, COCHRAN,
DAWN AND PHILLIP FROM MY
PREVIOUS ALLIANCE AND THE NEW
PEOPLE ARE MATT, JULIA AND THEN
THERE'S MICHAEL.
>> HELLO PHILIPPINES.
>> OH, DO I HAVE A SPECIAL PLACE
IN MY HEART FOR A GAY TKPWA.
IF I WASN'T AND MORON AND HASN'T
PLAYED THIS GAME BEFORE I'D TURN
ON MY ALLIANCE AND PLAY WITH THE
GAY BECAUSE I LIKE GAYS.
HOWEVER I WON'T DO THAT, NONE OF
MY PEOPLE ARE GOING TO FLIP,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> WE GOT A LITTLE DOWN TIME SO
THIS IS A GOOD TIME FOR ME TO
TALK TO YOU.
I HAD TO MAKE A BIG MOVE IN MY
SEASON WHERE I COMPLETELY
SWITCHED GEARS BECAUSE I WAS
READY TO BE -- YOU KNOW, A
DOUBLE AGENT IF I HAD TO BECAUSE
OBVIOUSLY I COULD JUST SIT PAT
AND SEE WHERE THINGS GO SENSE WE
HAVE THE NUMBERS OR I COULD MAKE
A BIG MOVE.
SO IF YOU WERE GOING TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE WITH ME, WE HAVE TO
MAKE SURE YOU SURVIVE AT LEAST
TO THE MERGE.
JULIA IS A 20-YEAR-OLD VERY,
VERY SMART NOT COLLEGE EDUCATED
LIKE MYSELF.
BUT SHE YOUNG.
SO I WANTED TO PLANT THE SEED
WITH HER BECAUSE IT WOULD
PROBABLY BE EASIER TO GET HER
TRUST THAN THE TWO MEN.
>> CAN I ASK WHAT YOU SEE IN ME
THAT'S HAVING YOU GIVE ME THIS
TALK?
>> I TEND TO LIKE PEOPLE WHO DO
THINGS THAT ARE, LIKE,
EXTRAORDINARY.
>> I THINK PHILLIP'S BEING A
GREAT STRATEGIC PLAYER GIVING A
LITTLE BIT OF INFORMATION AWAY
THAT COULD EITHER MAKE ME FEEL
REALLY COMFORTABLE AND EXCITED
OR SKEPTICAL AND HE KNOWS THAT
SO I'M HOPING TO BE ON HIS GOOD
PAGE BECAUSE I THINK THAT IT'S
ALWAYS NERVE-WRACKING TO GO WHEN
YOU HERE IN THE MINORITY.
>> I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU SOME
TIME TO THINK ABOUT THAT.
I PREFER YOU KEEP IT TO
YOURSELF.
>> I'LL DO MY BEST.
>> YOU'RE UNDER YOUR CONTROL.
I TOLD JULIA, PEOPLE CAN ADVANCE
AND MOVE AHEAD IN THIS GAME,
PARTICULARLY IF YOU'RE DOWN IN
THE NUMBERS.
I'M THE TYPE OF GUY THAT ONCE I
SAY SOMETHING, I'M GOING TO DO
THAT.
THE FLIP SIDE OF THAT IS, I'M
NOT GOING TO ASK TWICE.
MOST PEOPLE UNDERESTIMATE ME
BECAUSE OF MY PINK UNDERWEAR BUT
YOU'VE GOT TO BE READY TO MAKE A
MOVE WHEN IT COMES.
I LEARNED THAT FROM BEING A
FEDERAL AGENT.
>> THAT DIDN'T TAKE LONG.
>> I KNOW.
IT TOOK SECONDS.
>> THEY KIND OF JUST SLAMMED
HER.
>> THERE'S COMPLETE DIVIDE
BETWEEN THEM.
SHE'S PRETTY MUCH COMING TO US
BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T HAVE ANY --
>> SHE'S NOT TIGHT WITH THOSE
TWO SO THEY'RE NOT TOGETHER.
>> SO IF WE DID WANT HER AND WE
HAD TO SPLIT VOTES -- HE HAD AN
IDOL ALREADY AND HE'S LOOKING
FOR ANOTHER ONE.
>> HE HAD ONE AND PLAYED IT?
>> BECAUSE HE WAS SO PARANOID SO
IF HE FINDS ANOTHER IDOL --
>> SO FAR YOU COULDN'T ASK FOR
MORE FROM A DYSFUNCTIONAL GROUP
OF PEOPLE YOU'RE GOING TO JOIN
UP WITH.
SHERRY DEAD SET AGAINST EDDIE
AND REYNOLD.
THEY ARE BOTH GUNNING FOR EACH
OTHER WITHIN MINUTES OF US
HITTING THE BEACH.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE AN IDOL?
>> NO, I DON'T HAVE AN IDOL.
>> OH, DAMN IT.
>> IS THAT YOUR DREAM --
>> I'VE LOOKED.
>> ANDREA HAD A DREAM I HAD THE
IDOL LAST NIGHT.
IT'S SITTING ON MY WRIST RIGHT
NEXT TO HER HEAD.
I LOVE THIS GAME.
SHE'S A SMART GIRL BUT I'M AN
ACCOMPLISHED LIAR WHEN IT COMES
TO WOMEN SO MAYBE I PULLED IT
OFF.
>> THIS IS A PERFECT SCENARIO
FOR US.
A WE'LL HOPEFULLY WIN AND WE
COULD SPLIT THE VOTES JUST SO
THERE'S NO IDOL.
>> PERFECT!
>> IT'S FINE.
I'M HAPPY SO FAR.
I'M HAPPY WITH THE PLACE AND
THESE GUYS SEEM VERY, VERY NICE.
VERY CHILL.
SO WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS IN THE
NEXT 24 HOURS.
>> I HAD A QUIT CHAT WITH JULIA.
ARE YOU PLANNING TO MAKE BIG
MOVES IN THIS GAME?
PLANNING TO GET TO THE END?
BECAUSE AT THE MERGE THAT'S WHEN
EVERYTHING HAPPENS.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW WHO TO TALK TO
AND WHO YOU CAN TRUST.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN WORK WITH
US?
YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
AND SHE GOES YEAH, I'LL THINK
ABOUT IT.
>> BUT I'M NOT CONCERNED ABOUT
GETTING A FLIPPER.
WE DON'T NEED IT.
>> WITHIN I WOULD SAY 30 MINUTES
HE'S GOT JULIA IN A CORNER
TELLING HER SHE'S GOT TO FLIP IF
SHE WANTS A CHANCE IN THE
ALLIANCE, SHE COULD BE SEVENTH
PLACE.
YOU CAN'T SAY TO PHILLIP THAT
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE, WE DON'T
NEED SOMEBODY TO FLIP.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
HE'S THE WORST FEDERAL AGENT
I'VE EVER MET.
WHAT CASES DID HE CRACK?
LIKE, WHAT WAS HE WORKING ON?
IS THAT THE REASON OUR COUNTRY'S
IN SUCH A MESS?
LIKE, HONESTLY.
>> IN TRUE PHILLIP FASHION HE
COMES OVER TO ME AND IS LIKE I
HAVE TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
HE SAYS SO I TALKED TO JULIA
ABOUT FLIPPING.
I'M LIKE WHAT?
FOR SOMEBODY WHO IS SUPPOSED TO
BE ABLE TO READ PEOPLE, I'M
LYING ALL THE TIME TO HIM.
I CAN'T -- IT'S SO -- HE'S JUST
--
>> I'M JUST GLAD HE'S WITH US.
HE CAN'T BE LEFT ALONE.
>> I GUESS NOT.
DON'T THINK IT HASN'T CROSSED MY
HEAD TO TURN AROUND AND VOTE
PHILLIP OUT AND BE LIKE THE HELL
WITH HIM.
HE NEED A WARM GLASS OF SHUT THE
HELL UP.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> WE ARE.
>> Jeff: FIRST THING'S FIRST,
ANDREA.
TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY BACK UP FOR
GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE TWO
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL RACE
TO ROLL A CHARGE TRIBE-COLORED
CRATE BACK TO THE START.
THEN THE NEXT TWO GO.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL SIX
CRATES YOU MUST USE THEM TO
BUILD A STAIRCASE THAT SPELLS
"FANS VS. FAVORITES."
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE SENT
HOME.
WITH TWO NEW TRIBES AND NOBODY
CERTAIN WHERE THEY STAND, YOU DO
NOT WANT TO BE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: JULIA, EDDIE AND ERIC
LOOKING FOR THAT FIRST CRATE.
THEY ARE VERY HEAVY.
>> THAT'S IT, GUYS!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP AND JULIA
TAKING THEIR TIME.
EDDIE AND ERIC OFF TO A QUICK
START.
NOT MESSING AROUND.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: GOTA OFF TO AN EARLY
LEAD.
PHILLIP AND JULIA SLOWING DOWN
NOW.
EDDIE AND ERIC HAVE A NICE
RHYTHM MAKING THIS LOOK EASY.
>> DOING GREAT!
>> GO NOW!
TWO MORE, ONE MORE!
>> Jeff: HEAD OUT, GOTA.
GOTA HAS THEIR FIRST CRATE.
MALCOLM AND ANDREA HEADING OUT.
PHILLIP AND JULIA REALLY SLOWING
DOWN TOWARD THE END.
BIKAL FALLING BEHIND QUICKLY.
MALCOLM AND ANDREA COMING BACK
WITH THEIR SECOND CRATE.
>> YOU GOT IT, WE'RE ALMOST
THERE.
>> ONE MORE PUSH.
>> Jeff: BIKAL IS OUT TO THEIR
FIRST CRATE.
DAWN AND MICHAEL HEADING OUT.
>> GO, BABY!
>> Jeff: 16 DAYS OUT HERE,
VERY HEAVY CRATES TO PUSH.
MICHAEL AND DAWN TRYING TO MAKE
UP SOME TIME.
GOTA'S BACK, HEAD OUT.
GOTA HAS THEIR SECOND CRATE.
IT'S NOW REYNOLD AND BRENDA
HEADING OUT FOR THE THIRD CRATE
FOR GOTA.
BIKAL REALLY SLOWING DOWN.
MICHAEL AND DAWN GIVING IT WHAT
THEY'VE GOT BUT IT'S NOT A LOT.
REYNOLD FLYING.
GO!
NOW CORRINE AND MATT HEADING OUT
FOR BIKAL LOOKING FOR THAT THIRD
CRATE WHILE REYNOLD AND BRENDA
COME BACK WITH THE THIRD GREAT
FOR GOTA.
YOU'VE GOT SOME TIME TO MAKE UP,
PURPLE!
GO!
ERIK NOW HEADING OUT, SHERRI
GETTING INTO IT.
>> YOU GOT IT, YEAH!
>> Jeff: HEAD OUT, BIKAL WITH
THEIR THIRD CRATE.
PHILLIP HEADING BACK OUT WITH
COCHRAN THIS TIME.
SHERRI AND ERIK COMING BACK WITH
THAT FOURTH CRATE.
MALCOLM AND EDDIE HEADING OUT
FOR THE FIFTH CRATE FOR GOTA.
PHILLIP AND COCHRAN WORKING
TOGETHER ON THAT FOURTH CRATE.
>> HERE YOU GO, GUYS!
GO COCHRAN!
GO PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM AND EDDIE ARE
GOING TO TRY TO PASS PHILLIP AND
COCHRAN HERE.
>> PUSH!
>> GO!
>> Jeff: GOTA BACK WITH THEIR
FIFTH CRATE.
PHILLIP AND COCHRAN BACK WITH
THE FOURTH CRATE.
GO.
>> I'M NOT FOURTH.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP HAVING TO RUN
FOR A THIRD TIME!
>> I THOUGHT I WAS SIX.
NOT BACK TO BACK.
>> WE NEED YOU.
>> Jeff: STRANGE STRATEGY BY
BIKAL.
PHILLIP ON HIS THIRD PASS AND
IT'S SHOWING.
OLDEST GUY OUT HERE.
RED.
>> READY?
>> Jeff: GOTA HAS THEIR SIXTH
AND FINAL CRATE.
START WORKING ON THE STAIRCASE.
MICHAEL AND PHILIP ARE WALKING
THEIR FIFTH CRATE IN.
THEY'VE STILL GOT A SIXTH CRATE
WAITING.
BIG LEAD FOR GOTA RIGHT NOW.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
>> Jeff: THESE CRATES WEIGH A
LOT.
TO GET THEM TO THE TOP TAKES
EVERYBODY WORKING TOGETHER.
MICHAEL AND PHILLIP BACK.
DAWN AND MATT LETTING OUT FOR
THE SIXTH AND FINAL CRATE.
>> WASN'T I SIXTH?
>> Jeff: GOTA WORKING QUICKLY.
THEY THINK THINK THEY'VE GOTTEN
A IDEA GOING THAT'S RIGHT.
>> NEXT!
>> BRING IT UP.
COME ON!
>> Jeff: BIKAL WITH THEIR
SIXTH CRATE.
START WORKING ON YOUR STAIRCASE!
NOW'S WEAR TEAM WORK IS COMING
INTO PLAY.
YOU'RE LOOKING TO SPELL OUT
"FANS VS. FAVORITES."
I THINK THIS IS THE ONE WE WANT
UP THERE.
>> Jeff: JULIA IS CALLING
SHOTS FOR BIKAL.
MALCOLM CALLING THE SHOTS FOR
GO.
A HE SEEMS CERTAIN THAT HE IS
RIGHT.
GOTA HAS THREE IN PLACE.
IF THEY'RE RIGHT, THAT'S A BIG
LEAD.
>>S WHERE IT GOING?
>> IT'S GOING TO GO RIGHT UP
HERE.
RIGHT UP HERE.
>> F YOU THINK IT'S SOMEWHERE
LET'S PUT IT THERE.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO GET IT RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE MOVING AGAIN.
>> Jeff: BIKAL APPEARS TO BE
ON SOME SORT OF MEDICATION
THEY'RE MOVING SO SLOW.
>> THIS WAY.
>> Jeff: GOTA WORKING ON THEIR
FOURTH AND FIFTH CRATES AT THE
SAME TIME.
NEARLY KNOCKING REYNOLD OFF OF
THIS STRUCTURE.
>> THAT'S GOT TO GO AT THE VERY
TOP.
>> ALL OF US HAVE TO LIFT THIS
UP.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> Jeff: BIKAL FINALLY PUTTING
ONE CRATE IN PLACE.
>> COUNTERCLOCKWISE.
>> Jeff: GOTA HAS FIVE CRATES
IN PLACE.
ONE CRATE LEFT FOR GOTA.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> Jeff: BIKAL NEEDS TO BE
RIGHT AND THEY NEED TO START
MOVING QUICKLY.
>> THIS IS WRONG, GUYS.
>> BACKWARDS?
>> I THINK THIS IS LIKE THE VERY
FIRST ONE.
THIS SHOULD BE AT THE VERY, VERY
BOTTOM.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME?
>> Jeff: PUT THIS ONE IN THE
DEEP FREEZE.
THIS IS OVER.
>> FIVE, FIVE, FIVE!
>> Jeff: GOTA FINISHES.
GOTA WINS IMMUNITY!
(SCREAMING)
>> GREAT JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: THAT WAS PATHETIC.
>> IT SURE WAS.
>> GREAT JOB, GUYS, GREAT JOB.
>> YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING.
>> Jeff: GOTA, WHO WANTS IT?
CONGRATULATIONS.
(APPLAUSE)
GOTA, CONGRATULATIONS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
BIG WIN EARLY WITH THESE NEW
TRIBES.
DOMINATION BY GOTA.
BIKAL, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME.
>> CORRINE IS SO INEPT EXCEPT
TAKING CARE OF HER BODY.
AS FAR AS ANYTHING ELSE GOING ON
IT'S JUST EMPTY.
FAVORITES MUST DOMINATE FOR NOW.
WHAT WE WOULD SAY BACK IN THE
DAY WAS THE RESPONSES OF HUMAN
BEINGS VARY GREATLY UNDER
DANGEROUS CIRCUMSTANCES.
STRONG MEN ADVANCE ONLY, WEAK
MEN GROW AGITATED.
BUT SUPERIOR MEN THEY STAND
THEIR GROUND AND WAIT FOR BETTER
CHANCES.
THAT'S WHAT I'VE GOT TO DO HERE.
I'VE JUST GOT TO WAIT FOR THE
PROPER MOMENT AND GIVE HER THE
BOOT.
>> BEFORE WE DO THAT I WANT TO
SAY SOMETHING.
WE DID OUR BEST TODAY.
WE ACTUALLY DID GEL TOGETHER AS
A GROUP HERE IN CAMP.
WE'VE WORKED VERY EFFECTIVELY
TOGETHER.
I THINK WE ALL WENT IN THERE
THINKING WE COULD GO IN THERE
AND KICK SOME ASS BUT SOME DAYS
THE BETTER TEAM WINS.
>> PHILLIP IS THE MOST ANNOYING
PLAYER OUT HERE HANDS DOWN.
THE REASON WHY EVERYBODY KEEPS
THINKING HE'S THE RING LEADER IS
BECAUSE HE DOES OUTRAGEOUS
THINGS AND WE ALL JUST KEEP
QUIET ABOUT IT.
>> TODAY WAS THEIR DAY, YOU
KNOW?
THEY HAD MORE STRENGTH THAN WE
DID.
THEY CLEARLY GOT OFF TO A QUICK
START WITH US.
I DIDN'T SEE ANYBODY OUT THERE
ON OUR SIDE NOT PUTTING IN 110%.
WE WERE ALL RUNNING AND
STRUTTING BUT THEY WERE MOVING
THOSE BOXES LIKE THEY WERE
PAPERWEIGHTS.
>> I DON'T CARE.
I KNOW HE'S NOT THE LEADER AND I
KNOW I'M NOT GOING TO LISTEN TO
HIM BUT IF HE WANTS TO HAVE A
SPEECH, HAVE YOUR SPEECH.
ON A SCALE OF ONE TO ON AN
AIRPLANE NEXT TO A BABY ANNOYING
HE'S ON THE AIRPLANE NEXT TO THE
BABY ANNOYING AND THE BABY HAS
DIARRHEA.
IT'S THE MOST ANNOYING SITUATION
YOU CAN BE IN.
>> BUT I DON'T THINK WE HAVE TO
HOLD OUR HEAD LOW OR LIKE
SOMEBODY THREW THIS.
NONE OF US DID THAT.
I DON'T PLAY THAT WAY.
>> IT'S FRUSTRATING BUT THERE IS
LITTLE I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
AS ANNOYING AS HE IS, HE'LL VOTE
WITH ME AND HE AIN'T GONNA FLIP.
>> WHAT I SAW TODAY IS EVERYBODY
OUT THERE PUSHING, EVERYBODY
STEPPED UP.
SO HOLD OUR HEADS HIGH, WE'LL
GET HIM NEXT TIME.
OKAY?
>> THANKS, PHILLIP.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKINGS, FILL
TRIP?
>> HMM?
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> IN TERMS OF TONIGHT?
>> YUP.
>> I THINK A GIRL'S GOING TO GO.
>> THAT'S MY PLAN.
I WANTED TO SEE WHERE YOU WERE
COMING FROM.
I WANT TO BE HERE, DUDE, I WANT
TO MAKE IT TO THE MERGE, I WANT
TO BE A STRONG TRIBE.
>> WE'LL BET THEM NEXT TIME AND
MAKE IT TO THE MERGE.
>> YUP.
>> IS IT PLEAD OUR CASE TO
PHILLIP TIME?
>> I JUST WANTED TO SEE WHAT HE
THOUGHT.
>> I ALREADY TOLD HIM WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO.
WE HAVE TO VOTE OUT THE GIRL.
SHE GOT FLUSTERED AND IT WAS
CLEAR SHE GOT FLUSTERED BECAUSE
WE DIDN'T GET IT RIGHT.
THERE'S A PRICE TO BE PAID FOR
THAT.
PLUS I THINK YOU GUYS ARE BETTER
ASSETS GOING FORWARD STRENGTH
VERSUS STRENGTH AGAINST THEM THE
NEXT CHALLENGE.
WE GET TO THE MERGE, WE'LL BE
COUNTING ON YOU BECAUSE HERE'S
WHAT I WANT TO DO.
I STILL OPERATE STEALTH "R" US,
IT'S UP AND RUNNING.
I WON'T TELL YOU WHO THE MEMBERS
ARE BUT IT'S A FORCE TO BE
RECKONED WITH IN THIS GAME.
>> YUP.
>> WHEN I ACTUALLY INDUCT
SOMEONE INTO STEALTH "R" US
THEY'VE GIVEN A NAME AS YOU KNOW
FROM WATCHING MY SEASON.
YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE PEOPLE WITH
NAMES ALREADY OUT HERE.
SO YOUR TEST WILL BE YOU'RE
GOING TO PROBABLY BE TOLD BY
SOMEONE ELSE WITHIN MY TRIBE TO
DO SOMETHING.
UNLESS I TELL YOU DIFFERENTLY,
DO IT.
>> UNDERSTOOD.
>> SO DON'T WAIT FOR IT FROM YOU
--
>> IN OTHER WORDS, IF SOMEONE
ELSE TOLD YOU, YOU JUST
ACKNOWLEDGED WHAT THEY'VE SAID.
THERE IS TWO OF US THAT ARE
REALLY THE CONTROLLING FACTORS
AND WE DELIBERATELY SET IT UP
THAT WAY SO IF ONE OF US GOT OUT
OF THE GAME WE COULD STILL
OPERATE AS STEALTH "R" US, LIKE
ANY BACKUP PLAN YOU'D HAVE.
>> I WAS TRYING TO KEEP A
STRAIGHT FACE, BUT HEARING
PHILLIP TALK ABOUT THIS STEALTH
"R" US AND ALL THIS STUFF, IT
MADE ME WANT TO BUST OUT
LAUGHING.
BUT PHILLIP MAY BE A TICKET FOR
ME TO GET FARTHERRER IN THIS
GAME SO IF I HAVE TO KISS ASS
RIGHT NOW TO PHILLIP AND BE LIKE
"YES, MASTER, I'LL DO WHAT YOU
SAY."
IF THAT CAN GET KNOW THE MERGE
AND THE NEXT PROCESS IN THIS
GAME I'M GOING TO DO IT.
ENOUGH SAID.
>> AND THIS CONVERSATION WILL
NOT BE REPEATED AGAIN.
WHEN I SEE YOU'VE EXECUTED THE
VERY FIRST TASK I'VE GIVEN YOU,
YOU WILL THEN BECOME A MEMBER
ALONG WITH THE OTHER SIX MEMBERS
IN STEALTH "R" US.
>> (LAUGHS)
STEALTH "R" US.
>> DO I GET A T-SHIRT.
>> YOU DO, I HAVE T-SHIRTS AND
EVERYTHING.
ALL RIGHT.
>> YUP, MAN.
>> WHAT ARE WE SAYING TO SKWAOUL
YA?
>> I'M GOING ASK HER WHO SHE'S
VOTING FOR.
I'M GOING TO TELL HER THAT I'M
PLEADING MY CASE.
HELLO!
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUY THINKING IN
TERMS OF VOTING?
>> WE DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
THEY'RE THINKING, DUDE AND I
HAVE NO IDEA.
>> MY QUESTION IS DOWN TO DO WE
ALL VOTE FOR ONE?
>> YOU KNOW, ALL OF THEM HAVE
JUST BEEN LIKE, YOU KNOW, SORRY,
SORRY, SORRY.
>> THE BEST SCENARIO WOULD BE
THAT THEY WANT TO VOTE FOR ONE
OF THEIR PEOPLE AND THAT THEY
WOULD BRING US IN AND SAY WE
WANT YOUR VOTE TO GET RID OF
THIS PERSON.
>> WELL WHAT IF WE ALL JUST VOTE
FOR COCHRAN.
YOU DON'T LIKE THAT?
WHO THEN?
>> I WOULD ALMOST SAY DAWN.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, WHATEVER YOU GUYS DECIDE
IS FINE.
>> I THINK WE ALL VOTE FOR DAWN.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> OKAY.
>> COOL.
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
I'M GLAD WE GOT TO TALK.
>> RIGHT NOW JULIA THINKS THAT
MICHAEL AND MYSELF ARE GOING TO
WRITE DAWN'S NAME DOWN.
BUT I'M DEFINITELY NOT WRITING
DAWN'S NAME DOWN, I'M WRITING
JULIA WITH A CAPITAL "J."
AND TO BE HONEST, IT'S LIKE AS
LONG AS IT AIN'T ME GOING HOME,
THAT'S ALL I GIVE A CRAP ABOUT.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS, I THINK
YOU'RE GREAT AND IF I WAS ON
YOUR TRIBE FROM THE BEGINNING
MORE THAN LIKELY I'D BE IN AN
ALLIANCE WITH THE TWO OF YOU.
HOWEVER WE DON'T KNOW.
EVERYONE'S PLAYING "SURVIVOR" SO
IT'S REALLY, REALLY DIFFICULT.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND SO, LIKE, WHO ARE YOU
GUYS GOING TO VOTE?
>> WHAT I WAS GOING TO SAY WAS,
LIKE, YOU TELL ME HOW TO VOTE.
THAT'S -- YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YOU TELL ME.
>> OUR FEAR IS ALWAYS, LIKE, IF
WE DIVULGE THE INFORMATION AND
SOMEONE HAS THE IDOL WE BLOW
EVERYTHING.
>> WELL, I CAN TELL YOU.
OBVIOUSLY PEOPLE LIE TO YOUR
FACE IN "SURVIVOR."
I DON'T HAVE THE DAMN IDOL.
IF I DID I WOULD PLAY IT TONIGHT
AND NOT GIVE IT TO HIM.
>> IT SEEMS RELATIVELY CLEAR TO
ME THAT ONE OF THE FANS IS GOING
TO GO HOME TONIGHT.
I KIND OF LIKE THE IDEA OF
VOTING OFF JULIA.
BUT A POSSIBLE DOWN SIDE IS THAT
MATT AND MICHAEL ARE OPENLY VERY
CLOSE TO EACH OTHER SO LEAVING
AN OUTSPOKEN DUO, A POWER COUPLE
IN THIS GAME DOESN'T SEEM TO
MAKE THAT MUCH STRATEGIC SENSE.
>> MICHAEL AND I, WE'VE BEEN
GUNG-HO ON STARTING FRESH, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WE HAVEN'T REALLY TALKED A LOT
STRATEGY WISE SO I DON'T KNOW
WHERE PHILLIP LIES, IF HE'S THE
KINGPIN AND THIS AND THAT.
>> MATT I'M PRETTY SURE HE
DOESN'T HAVE THE IDOL, HE REEKS
OF DESPERATION.
BUT IT SEEMS BETWEEN MATT AND
JULIA.
WHO KNOWS?
IF AN IDOL IS PLAYED, MAYBE IT'S
ME, MAYBE IT'S CORRINE.
MAYBE IT'S PHILLIP.
>> THE ORIGINAL PLAN IS GOING TO
BE JULIA.
THINKING ABOUT IT, MICHAEL AND
MATT SEEM MUCH CLOSER TO EITHER
OF THEM TO JULIA.
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS
WHO HAS THE IDOL.
>> MATT DOESN'T.
>> NO, MATT DOESN'T.
>> 100% DOES NOT.
>> WE STAY IN THE GAME IF WE
KEEP MATT.
>> AND ANY BREAKUP --
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> MATT'S GOT TO GO.
>> WHY, BECAUSE YOU THINK HE HAS
IT?
>> I DON'T THINK ANY OF THEM DO
BUT I KNOW MATT DOESN'T.
>> BY I THINK IT SHOULD BE THE
GIRL BECAUSE I THINK THAT WE
HAVE A CHANCE TO TURN BOTH OF
THESE TWO.
>> THAT'S KIND OF WHERE I WAS
AT.
>> I THINK WE CAN TURN THEM.
>> TONIGHT'S VOTE IS KIND OF AS
TOUP BETWEEN MATT AND JULIA.
I MEAN, I WILL SAY I'M GLAD MY
GAY GOT SAVED.
GOD SAVE THE GAY.
I AM UNDECIDED.
I WOULD LOVE TO GET RID OF JULIA
BECAUSE, A, SHE'S REALLY BORING.
AND, B, LIKE, SHE REALLY IS THE
ONE THAT COST US THE CHALLENGE.
THE THING IS, I REALLY, REALLY
LIKE MATT.
MATT CAME TO ME, HE WAS HONEST
WITH ME, DOESN'T HAVE THE IDOL,
I'M CONVINCE HEAD DOESN'T HAVE
THE IDOL.
WHY WILL I PUNISH HIM WHEN JULIA
HASN'T SAID TWO WORDS TO ME?
SHE DOESN'T CONTRIBUTE ANYTHING
EXCEPT A NASALLY VOICE.
SO I'M ABOUT GETTING RID OF HER.
IT'S REALLY HARD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
Jeff: SO, MATT, WHEN YOU
GUYS FINALLY CAME TOGETHER AND
THERE ARE FANS NOW WITH
FAVORITES, WHAT'S THAT LIKE FOR
YOU BEING SUCH A FAN OF THE
GAME?
>> I WAS SUPER STOKED.
LIKE I WAS A BIG FAN OF COCHRAN
AND PHILLIP AND DAWN AND CORRINE
SO IT WAS PRETTY SURREAL AND I
COULDN'T BE HAPPIER WITH THIS
GROUP OF PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: JULIA, THE OBVIOUS
QUESTION IS FOUR FAVORITES,
THREE FANS.
ARE THE FANS IN TROUBLE?
>> WELL, I DEFINITELY THINK THAT
IT WOULD BE SILLY TO THINK THE
FANS WEREN'T IN A LITTLE BIT OF
TROUBLE.
WE ARE THE MINORITY.
THE FAVORITES HAVE THE NUMBERS
SO THERE'S A LITTLE BIT OF A
DIVIDE.
>> Jeff: IS THERE A SENSE,
MICHAEL, THEN THAT IT IS YOU,
JULIA, OR MATT GOING HOME
TONIGHT?
>> 100%, YES.
ONE OF US IS GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: NO QUESTION?
>> NOT IN MY MIND.
>> Jeff: CORRINE, HAVE THERE
BEEN ANY BONDS MADE THAT MAKE IT
HARD-- EVEN THOUGH THIS IS A
GAME-- TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR FIRST
IMPRESSION OF MICHAEL.
>> YOU KNOW I ALWAYS LIKE TO
PLAY WITH A GAY.
I WAS THRILLED.
AND THE MORE I GOT TO KNOW THE
TWO OF THEM IT WAS THE SAME
THING.
IT WAS ACTUALLY SO OVERWHELMING
FOR ME BECAUSE I WAS, LIKE, GOD
THERE ARE AT LEAST THREE PEOPLE
I'D REPLACE IN MY OWN ALLIANCE.
THEY'RE GREAT, GREAT PEOPLE.
AND I STRUGGLE WITH THE FACT
THAT THIS DECISION TONIGHT ISN'T
NECESSARILY A FAIR ONE.
IT'S VERY HARD FOR ME.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, WHAT'S THE
CURRENCY THAT HELPED YOU DECIDE
WHO SHOULD WE KEEP TONIGHT
BETWEEN MATT, JULIA, AND
MICHAEL?
>> THE NUMBER-ONE THING I'M
GOING TO BE LOOKING FOR IS ARE
YOU LOYAL, ARE YOU TRUSTWORTHY
AND CAN YOU DO CHALLENGES?
WHEN WE GET TO THE MERGE IF I
ASK YOU TO DO SOMETHING CAN YOU
DO WHAT I ASK YOU TO DO?
>> Jeff: CORRINE, HOW DO YOU
ASSES WHO TO GET RID OF?
YOU'RE IN A GREAT SPOT.
THERE ARE FOUR FAVORITES.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO MINCE WORDS.
I'M PARANOID ABOUT THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND, YEAH, SURE,
IT LOOKS GOOD WHEN YOU'RE 4-3
BUT IT JUST TAKES ONE IMMUNITY
IDOL TO SEND ONE OF US HOME.
>> TRUE.
>> AND IT'S ENTIRELY POSSIBLE
ONE OF THE THREE OF THEM HAVE
IT.
SURELY THEY'RE NOT GOING TO TELL
ME.
CLEARLY THEY WANT ME TO TELL
THEM WHO I'M VOTING FOR BECAUSE
THAT WOULD BE THE BEST WAY TO
POSITION THE IDOL BUT YOU CAN'T
GIVE UP ANY INFORMATION BECAUSE
THAT'S DANGEROUS.
>> Jeff: SO, MATT, WHAT DO YOU
DO WHEN CORRINE IS BEING PRETTY
HONEST AND SAYING, LISTEN, I'M
WORRIED SO EITHER TELL ME THE
TRUTH AND CONVINCE ME OR TELL ME
A LIE AND CONVINCE ME BUT YOU'VE
GOT TO CONVINCE ME.
>> WELL, WE TALKED TODAY ABOUT
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I KNOW SHE'S BEEN WORRIED ABOUT
IT AND I HAVE NOTHING TO HIDE.
I TOLD HER I DON'T HAVE IT AND I
ALSO THINK SOME OF MY TRIBE
MATES WOULD HAVE TOLD ME IF THEY
HAD THE IDOL AND I WOULD HAVE
TOLD CORRINE WHO HAD IT.
>> AGAIN, THIS IS "SURVIVOR"
101.
IF I'M THEN, WE HAVE ONE SHOT TO
TURN THIS AROUND.
IF WE'VE GOT ONE IDOL BETWEEN
THE THREE OF US, WE PLAY OUR
CARDS RIGHT WE CAN GET SOME
FOOTING HERE.
AND I DO TRUST THAT HE DOESN'T
HAVE IT.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY IT'S NOT THAT
SIMPLE.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, CORPS VIN
VERY CONCERNED.
>> I'M VERY CONCERNED ABOUT THE
IDOL, TOO.
THE WAY WE'LL APPROACH THIS
DECISION IS BASED ON WHETHER OR
NOT WE THINK YOU HAVE THE IDOL
OR NOT.
SOUF SO IF YOU HAVE IT YOU'RE
GOING TO PLAY IT.
IF YOU DON'T YOU'LL PROBABLY BE
GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, HOW DO YOU
DETERMINE WHO YOU'LL GET RID OF?
IF YOU GET TO A MERGE YOU MIGHT
NEED THOSE TWO PEOPLE.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING
ON THE OTHER TRIBE.
>> THAT'S THE BIG THING,
ACTUALLY.
WE DON'T WANT TO KEEP LOSING
BECAUSE THE MORE WE KEEP LOSING
THE CLOSER THEY'RE GETTING ON
THE OTHER TRIBE, THEY'RE LIKE
THE BOLD AND THE BEAUTIFUL
GROUP.
I DON'T SEE ME NECESSARILY
PENETRATING THAT GROUP.
SO THE MAIN THING IS LOYALTY AND
TRUST AS PHILLIP SAID IN A MERGE
SITUATION BUT IT'S NOT AN
ENVIABLE CHOICE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE THERE ARE REALLY ALL
GOOD OPTIONS.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
PHILLIP, YOU'RE UP.
>> MY VOTE IS FOR YOU, JULIA.
I HOPE IT'S YOU AND NOT ME
TONIGHT.
>> DARLING, YOU KNOW I THINK
YOU'RE GREAT, I'M JUST TRYING TO
LIVE TO SEE ONE MORE DAY.
>> I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT
TO-TO-PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE
TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JULIA.
TWO VOTES JULIA.
DAWN.
TWO VOTES JULIA; ONE VOTE DAWN.
MATT.
ONE VOTE MATT.
THAT'S TWO VOTES MATT.
MATT.
THREE VOTES MAT; TWO VOTES
JULIA; ONE VOTE DAWN.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"FANS VS. FAVORITES" MATT, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
MATT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> SEE YOU GUYS.
>> SEE YOU, MAN.
>> Jeff: WELL IF TONIGHT'S
VOTE IS ANY INDICATION, JULIA,
MICHAEL, NEW TROUBLE.
THE ONLY WAY YOU STAY IN THIS
GAME, YOU HAVE TO WIN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
PHILLIP TALKS THE TALK.
>> ANYTHING TO DO WITH THE UPPER
BODY I'M ALMOST CERTAIN I CAN
WIN IT.
>> Jeff: BUT CAN'T WALK THE
WALK.
>> I CAN'T RUN, I'M TIRED.
>> Jeff: WHILE MALCOLM'S GAME
IS JUST GETTING STARTED.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE LOOK
ON PEOPLE'S FACES WHEN I TAKE
CONTROL OF THIS GAME IN JUST A
FEW SHORT DAYS.
GOD I CAN'T WAIT!
>> YOU KNOW, I CAME INTO THIS
GAME KNOWING THAT MY SOCIAL GAME
WOULD BE MY STRONG POINT.
I GOT ALONG WITH EVERYBODY.
NO ONE THOUGHT, OH, THIS GUY IS
CRAZY OR TOO GNARLY BECAUSE HE
HAS A BEARD AND TATTOOS.
EVERYONE ACCEPTED ME FOR WHO I
WAS.
I PLAYED TO WIN.
I PUT ALL THE CARDS ON THE TABLE
AND I GOT VOTED OUT BUT I REALLY
DON'T REGRET ANYTHING.