>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": 10 OF SURVIVOR'S
BIGGEST FANS WERE PITTED AGAINST
10 FAVORITES FROM SEASONS PAST.
>> I'M READY, BABY.
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO
"SURVIVOR:FANS VERSUS FAVORITES
2."
AND RIGHT AWAY, THE FAVORITES
WANTED TO SHOW THE FANS WHO WAS
BOSS.
FAVORITES WIN THE FIRST
CHALLENGE!
>> WHILE THE FAVORITES FELT
RIGHT AT HOME.
>> I'M LOOKING AT EVERYBODY AND
THINKING THIS WILL BE A GOOD
GAME.
>> THE FANS STRUGGLE TO ADAPT.
>> I'M DEHYDRATED.
>> Jeff: THEY HAD NO FIRE,
COULDN'T COEXIST--
>> I BUST MY ASS WHILE YOU'RE
SITTING THERE.
>> SHUT UP!
>> Jeff: AND ALLIANCES BEGAN
TO PULL THEM APART.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE THIS FOUR
WITH ME, EDDIE, ALLIE AND HOPE.
>> YOU AND I WILL DECIDE WHICH
WAY WE WANT TO GO.
>> Jeff: BUT THINGS TURNED
AROUND FOR THE FANS.
>> FIRE!
>> Jeff: THEY GOT FIRE, AND
THEY WON THE FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FANS WIN!
WITH THE FAVORITES FACING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, PHILLIP AND FRANCESCA
REIGNITED THEIR AGE-OLD FEUD.
>> HE'S THE CRAZY PERSON.
>> SHE ANNOYS ME GREATLY.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP REINSTATED
THE "STEALTH R US" ALLIANCE,
TARGETING FRANCESCA WHILE
FRANCESCA PUT TOGETHER AN
ANTI-PHILLIP COALITION LEAVE,
COCHRAN AND DAUN IN THE MIDDLE.
>> WE NEED TO DECIDE WHICHEVER
ALLIANCE IS BEST FOR US.
>> WHEREVER COCHRAN AND I ALIGN,
WE KIND OF SWING.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
HISTORY WAS MADE WHEN FRANCESCA
BECAME THE ONLY SURVIVOR TO BE
VOTED OUT FIRST TWICE.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> AGAIN.
>> Jeff: 19 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
I UNDERSTAND IF YOU'RE UPSET
TOTALLY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW I
GENUINELILY OUTSIDE OF THIS
GAME--
>> THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT
TWICE IN A ROW, THAT'S THE
HARSHEST THING I HAVE EVER SEEN
IN MY LIFE.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT FIRST
TIME TWICE.
>> THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL SUCKED.
FRANCHESKA ONE OF THE NICEST
PERSON I'VE MET THE FIRST PERSON
TO BE HOLE.
>> DON'T BE MEAN, BRANDON.
>> I'M BEING VICIOUS.
THIS IS NOT ME.
THIS IS REALLY NICE, ACTUALLY.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO FIGHT.
>> WELL, OBVIOUSLY, YOU ARE.
>> NO, I'M TRYING TOW HAVE YOU
UNDERSTAND.
>> YOU'RE MAKING EXCUSES, DAUN.
>> I'M TRYING TO SAY HAVE
COMPASSION FOR BOTH SIDE OF A
STORY INSTEAD OF JUST YOURSELF.
>> I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU 'CAUSE
YOU'RE STILL GOING TO LOSE.
THAT'S WHAT I HAVE COMPASSION
ABOUT.
YOU'LL REMEMBER THIS
CONVERSATION ON THE BEACH.
BOTH OF YOU WILL LOSE BECAUSE OF
THAT STUPID MOVE.
>> FEEL LIKE BRANDON WAS REALLY
AWFUL TO ME AFTER WE CAME HOME
FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT JUST BECAME KIND OF TOO
POINTED AND PERSONAL FOR ME AND
I LITERALLY HAD TO WALK AWAY.
I HAVE TO GET A GRIP ON MY
EMOTIONS.
I DON'T WANT TO BE AROUND
EVERYONE CRYING.
IN
>> I TRY SO HARD TO NOT
DISRESPECT PEOPLE.
I JUST GET REALLY ARE LET
DOWN.
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT TO SOMEONE
SO TO HAVE SOMEONE DO IT TO ME,
MY BRAIN CAN'T PROCESS IT.
I'M LIKE, "OH, YOU'RE MEAN."
BUT IT'S ABOUT ME AND WHAT I
STAND FOR, AND IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER WHAT BRANDON THINKS OF
ME.
IT JUST DOESN'T.
BUT THAT'S REALLY DISAPPOINTING
BECAUSE IF HE TREATS OTHER
PEOPLE LIKE THAT, IT'S LIKE
POLLUTION.
OH...
>> I'M FED UP.
FED UP.
I'M GETTING A LITTLE REVENGEFUL,
OKAY.
>> YEAH.
>> THIS IS MY THOUGHT.
>> WHAT'S YOUR THOUGHT?
>> I'M THINKING OF GOING RUSSELL
HANTZ STYLE.
I'M SERIOUS.
I'M SO FREAKING PISSED OFF RIGHT
NOW.
>> I'M EXCITED.
>> I FEEL LIKE RAMBO.
LIKE, I HONESTLY FEEL MY UNCLE'S
BLOOD RUNNING THROUGH MY BODY
RIGHT NOW.
LIKE IT'S-- LIKE THE WAVE.
AND IT'S COMING BACK.
IT FEELS GREAT!
JUST IT WOULD BE REALLY FUN TO
SCREW THINGS UP.
>> IT WOULD BE.
>> JUST MAKE CAMP LIFE
MISERABLE.
I'LL MAKE RUSSELL LOOK LIKE A
LITTLE ( BLEEP ).
>> A LITTLE BABY?
>> YES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO OUT
BLINDSIDED.
THIS IS A GAME AND I'M PLAYING
IT DIRTY, TO THE CORE.
I WANT TO GO OUT WITH A BANG!
♪ IT'S GOOD ON THE ISLAND ♪ ♪
I'VE BEEN STAYING IN THE SHADE,
CONSERVING MY ENERGY.
I'M NOT REALLY TRYING TO DO TOO
MUCH, JUST KIND OF, YOU KNOW,
KEEP LOW BECAUSE I CAN'T KEEP
GETTING CAUGHT UP IN THESE,
LIKE, LITTLE SCUFFLES OVER
STUFF.
LIKE, I'M NOT GOING TO ARGUE
WITH YOU OVER WATER.
NOBODY IS WORRIED ABOUT MY
HYDRATION BUT ME.
SO I'VE BEEN RELAXING UNDER THE
TENT A LITTLE BIT.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO TALK ANY
MORE.
I JUST HAVE TO LAY HERE AND
PEOPLE GET CRAZY.
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE OUT IN THE
SUN.
I HAVE BEEN TO IRAQ TWICE SO I00
HOW TO DEAL WITH TIME.
I CAN SIT IN THE SHADE THE NEXT
FOUR DAYS.
ONCE THEY SEE I DON'T REALLY
CARE ABOUT THE GAME, THEN I'M
NOT REALLY A THREAT.
>> HALF THE DAY HE SLEEPS, AND
THE OTHER HALF HE SITS.
>> HONESTLY, HE IS SO LAZY.
IF WE WERE TO VOTE HIM OFF, I
DON'T THINK HE WOULD GUESS.
>> IT'S A GROUP JOKE, "WHERE IS
SHAMAR?
20 BUCKS SAYS HE'S NAPPING."
SHAMAR HAS TO GO IF WE GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT'S NONNEGOTIABLE.
>> SO TONIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> MIKE?
>> LAURA, JULIA.
>> OKAY.
>> AND THEN MATT.
>> YEAH.
>> I CAN TELL YOU NOW THAT THEY
WANT YOU WITH US.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M GOOD.
I'M TOTALLY DOWN WITH THAT.
>> I FEEL GOOD ABOUT THE SIX.
LAURA, JULIA, SHAMAR, MIKE, AND
MATT.
WE ARE SOLID.
THAT'S MY GANG.
AND SO IT'S US SIX AGAINST THE
FOUR-SOME, THE COUPLES, THE
LOVERS, THE WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
CALL THEM.
JUST KEEP TALKING AND RUNNING
YOUR MOUTH, WHICH YOU'RE GOOD
AT, BITCHING ABOUT WATER.
JUST KEEP DOING THAT.
DON'T GET PARANOID IF I'M NOT
STANDING BESIDE YOU OR HANGING
WITH YOU.
I'M NOT LETTING GO OF MY BOY
SHAMAR.
HE NEEDS TO BE RIGHT HERE IN MY
BACK POCKET.
I WANT SHAMAR TO KEEP ANNOYING
PEOPLE.
SHAMAR IS MY PHILLIP.
SO I WANT TO KEEP MY PHIL
AROUND, AND I GET ALONG WITH MY
PHIL.
I CAN-- I CAN STROKE HIM AND I
CAN-- I CAN PUT HIM BACK IN
PLACE.
I'M TELLING YOU, WE NEED YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> WE WANT YOU ON OUR SIDE.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS!
I LOVE YOU!
>> AFTER LAST NIGHT, IT MAKES ME
A LITTLE BIT FURTHER DOWN ON THE
TOTEM POLE.
>> RIGHT, WHAT I'M SAYING IS THE
MAIN FOCUS RIGHT NOW WE ALL
AGREE IS GOING TO HAVE TO BE
BUILDING, LIKE, A UNANIMOUS
COHESION.
>> JUST KEEP THIS BETWEEN-- I
WAS PLANNING ON SABOTAGING
EVERYTHING.
>> BY DOING WHAT?
>> SPILLING BEANS?
LOSING CHALLENGES.
AND THEN BE LIKE, YOU KNOW WHAT,
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN WIN THIS
WITHOUT ME, DO IT?
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING AND I WAS
LIKE,UN WHAT?
WHAT KIND OF PERSON WOULD I BE
KNOWN AS?
NOT A GOOD ONE.
>> RIGHT.
>> I WOULD BE KNOWN AS A
QUITTER.
AND THIS IS FOR MY KIDS.
THIS IS FOR MY CHILDREN.
I WAS LIKE THE BEST THING I CAN
DO IS TO BE NICE.
>> ONE OF THE MOST FRIGHTENING
THINGS ABOUT BRANDON'S
PERSONALITY IS HE HAS THESE
MOMENTS OF EXTREME RAGE AND
THEY'RE ALMOST IMMEDIATELY
FOLLOWED BY UNBELIEVABLY
PLEASANTNESS, SORT OF BEHAVIOR
FITTING A MURDERER WHO IS KIND
OF SOCIOPATHIC.
>> I LIKE OUR TRIBE, I REALLY
DO.
PHILLIP, YOU'RE NOT INTERRUPTING
NOTHING.
>> OKAY.
>> ONLY THING I CAN PREDICT
ABOUT BRANDON IS HE IS GOING TO
BE UNPREDICTABLE.
THAT GIVES ME VERY LITTLE SALOS
IN THIS GAME WHERE
PREDICTABILITY IS EVERYTHING.
>> WE WERE TALKING ABOUT WE WANT
TO BE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE, BUT
LIKE DIRECT A VOTE TOWARDS
SOMEBODY, NOT SO DIVIDED.
>> BOSTON ROB WOULD ALWAYS SAY
TO ME, "THIS IS WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO.
DISPIVMENT REALIZED HE DID THAT
TO MI MINIMIZE THE FLOW OF
INFORMATION.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU COULD
TRUST ME WITH THE FLOW OF
INFORMATION?
>> RIGHT NOW WHEN I GO, "HM,
TRUST OR NOT TRUST FULLY?
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH DATA YET."
I PAUSE.
I PAUSE WITH YOU.
A LOT OF TIMES PEOPLE DO A GREAT
JOB AND WANT TO BE THE CEO OF A
COMPANY AND THEY DON'T HAVE THE
PATIENCE TO SAY YOU HAVE TOW
START AT A LOWER LEVEL, MIDDLE
MANAGEMENT, SO RIGHT NOW--
>> I'M IN MIDMANAGEMENT.
>> AND THE C.E.O. DON'T CALL IN
MIDMANAGEMENT UNLESS HE HAS
SOMETHING HE WANTS TO TELL HIM.
BRANDON, HE IS NARCISSISTIC.
AND YOU'RE DEAL WITH A
NARCISSISTIC PERSON THEY DON'T
HAVE EMPATHY FOR OTHER PEOPLE.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THERE'S
SOMETHING VERY DISTURBING ABOUT
TO ME, I THINK-- I THINK SOMEONE
USED THE PHRASE FOR ME LAST
YEAR, CRAZY.
>> I'M GOING TO BE HONEST WITH
YOU, GUYS, PHILLIP IS PROBABLY
THE BIGGEST BULLY I HAVE EVER
MET IN MY LIFE.
>> WHAT?
>> HE'S MAKING ME REAL REALLY
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> HE'S CALLING HIMSELF THE
C.E.O. OF THE TRIBE.
YOU CAN'T TRUST ME BECAUSE OF
LAST SEASON AND I HAVE A FEEL
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN AGAIN.
I'M JUST SAYING.
YOU DON'T WANT TO FIGHT WITH ME!
SPECIAL AGENT PINK PANTHER WAS
FREAKING INSPECTOR GADGET
THOUGHT HE COULD PULL HIS
SPECIAL AGENT TRICK AND THAT IS
GOING TO BE THE DOWNED FALL IN
THIS GAME.
THE SIMPLE MATTER IS HE IS
TREATING PEOPLE LIKE GARBAGE.
HE IS STARTING TO "BOSTON ROB"
US A LITTLE BIT AND I DON'T LIKE
THAT.
YOU HAVE TO CUT THE HEAD OFF THE
SNAKE.
HE'S THE LEADER I'M NOT TRYING
TO--
>> LISTEN, HE'S NOT ANY KIND OF
LEADER.
>> WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT I
HAVE TO GIVE IT EVERYTHING I
HAVE THESE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
IF I DON'T, I'M GONE.
>> I'VE BEEN IN THE OUTSIDE.
I FEEL LIKE THERE'S STILL ROOM
FOR EVERYBODY TO WORK.
THAT'S THE WAY THIS GAME GOES.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
FANS GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW FAVORITES TRIBE.
FRANCESCA VOTED OUT AT THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WOW.
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> Jeff: THAT'S A FAVORITE.
MICHAEL, HUGE REACTION WHEN YOU
SAW IT WAS FRANCESCA THAT HAD
BEEN VOTED OUT FIRST.
>> THEY CAME TO PLAY.
THEY ARE VICIOUS PEOPLE, I CAN
TELL.
SHE WAS FIRST OFF IN HER OTHER
SEASON, AND THEY SENT HER HOME
FIRST.
NO MERCY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JULIA.
TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, THREE
MEMBERS FROM EACH TRIBE WILL
RACE TO A RAFT.
THEN THREE OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL PULL THAT RAFT OUT TO A
PLATFORM.
YOU'LL THEM DIVE DOWN WHERE YOU
WILL FIND A CAGE.
YOU'LL BEGIN REMOVING BAMBOO
STICKS, RELEASING RINGS.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL NINE
RINGS, YOU'LL BE PULLED BACK TO
SHORE AND THE THREE REMAINING
TRIBE MEMBERS WILL USE THOSE
RINGS, ATTEMPTING TO LAND THEM
ON A POST.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET ONE RING ON
EACH OF THE THREE POSTS WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
LOSERS WILL VOTE SOMEBODY OUT OF
THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: YOU EACH HAVE FIRE.
YOU EACH HAVE A BOAT.
THIS SHOULD MAKE IT POSSIBLE NOW
TO DO A LITTLE FISHING AND PUT
IT ALL TO GOOD WORK.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: A COMPLETE FISHING
KIT-- MASKS, SNORKEL, YOU HAVE
FISHING LINE, YOU HAVE FISHING
NET.
YOU HAVE A HAWAIIAN SLING.
FANS, YOU HAVE AN EXTRA PERSON.
YOU'RE SITTING SOMEBODY OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
>> I'M SITTING OUT, JEFF.
LAURA, TAKE A SEAT ON THE BENCH.
I'LL GIVE EVERYBODY ELSE A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
>> SWIMMER, SWIMMER, PULL, PULL.
>> WE NEED GOOD TALKERS.
I'M NOT A GOOD TALKER.
>> SO WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING?
>> ONE STRONG PERSON SHOULD GO
OUT IN CASE THEY'RE TOUGH TO
PULL OUT.
>> I DON'T THINK THEY'LL BE
TOUGH TO PULL OUT.
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I'M JUST GOING TO PULL.
BECAUSE MY IDEAS NEVER WORK.
I'M JUST A FOOL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO!
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GOT ERIK, ANDREA, AND BRENDA ON
THE RAFT FOR THE FAVORITES.
SHERRI, HOPE, AND JULIA ON THE
RAFT FOR THE FANS.
FAVORITES OUT QUICKLY.
BRANDON, CORINNE AND COCHRAN ARE
PULLING FOR THE FAVORITES.
SHAMAR, PAT AND EDDIE PULLING
FOR THE FANS.
>> YOU GRIEZ GAINING ON THEM!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: GOOD TEAM WORK BY
FANS AND FAVORITES.
WE'RE DEAD EVEN.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN AND YOU'RE
PULLING OUT BAMBOO STICKS TRYING
TO RELEASE RINGS.
ERIK IN THE WATER FOR THE
FAVORITES.
FAVORITES HAVE THEIR FIRST RING.
>> KEEP GOING.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: FANS HAVE THEIR FIRST
RING.
FAVORITES WITH THEIR SECOND
THERE ARE NINE RINES YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR.
>> SWITCH OUT!
>> Jeff: SHERRI STILL THE ONLY
PERSON IN THE WATER FOR THE
FANS, TRYING TO DO IT ALL
HERSELF.
FAVORITES WITH THEIR THIRD RING.
FANS HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE.
FAVORITES WITH THEIR FOURTH
RING.
FAVORITES DOING A GOOD JOB OF
ROTATING AND EVERYBODY'S COMING
UP WITH A RING.
HOPE'S NOW GOING TO GO IN.
>> LET'S GO, GUYS!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES WITH THEIR
SIXTH RING.
THE FANS STILL HAVE ONE RING.
FANS WITH THEIR SECOND RING!
FAVORITES WITH THEIR SEVENTH
RING.
THEIR EIGHTH RING.
>> GET READY, GUYS!
GET READY!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES HAVE ALL
NINE RINGS.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK.
>> WAY TO GO GOTA.
>> Jeff: FANS REALLY
STRUGGLING TO GET SOMETHING
GOING.
>> WHAT ARE THEY DOING OUT
THERE?
>> Jeff: FANS WITH THEIR THIRD
RING.
FOURTH RING.
FIFTH RING.
THEY'VE STILL GOT FOUR TO GO AND
THE FAVORITES ARE ALREADY
HALFWAY BACK.
>> LET'S GO!
>> LET'S GO, GUYS!
>> Jeff: FANS WITH THEIR SIXTH
RING.
SEVENTH RING.
FAVORITES ARE ALL THE WAY BACK.
FANS WITH THEIR EIGHTH RING.
THEY'VE STILL GOT ONE LEFT.
JULIA NOW IN THE WATER.
>> DOP IT.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES JUST NEED
TO LAND THREE RINGS TO WIN.
>> LET'S GO.
BRING IT UP.
>> Jeff: FANS HAVE THEIR NINTH
RING.
GET ON THE RAFT, START PULLING!
FANS NEED TO PICK IT UP!
>> MALCOLM TOSSING FOR THE
FAVORITES.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES HAVE THEIR
FIRST RING.
FAVORITES HAVE THEIR SECOND
RING.
FAVORITES JUST NEED TO LAND ONE
MORE RING.
FANS AREN'T EVEN BACK TO SHORE
YET.
>> GET OFF!
GET OFF!
>> Jeff: FANS BACK NOW REYNOLD
TOSSING FOR THE FANS.
LANDS ONE FOR THE FANS.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM COULD WIN IT
RIGHT HERE FOR THE FAVORITES.
JUST MISSES.
OPENING THE DOOR FOR THE FANS.
IMMUNITY AND A BIG REWARD ON THE
LINE.
>> COME OMIKE, YOU'RE CLOSE,
YOU'RE CLOSE!
>> Jeff: HERE'S PHILLIP.
>> AH!
>> GO, GO, GO!
GET THEM, GET THEM, GET THEM!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP COULD DO IT
RIGHT HERE!
PHILLIP SCORES, FAVORITES WIN
IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
>> YEAH, BABY!
AARRGGHH!
>> Jeff: FAVORITE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> YES!
( APPLAUSE )
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES, NO TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
IN ADDITION, HUGE FISHING
REWARD.
COME GET IT.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
ALL RIGHT, FANS, TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT, WHERE ONE OF THE 10 OF
YOU WILL BE THE SECOND PERSON
VOTED OUT THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> I WAS THINKING LESS ABOUT THE
EXPLOS MORE THAT SHAMAR HAS GOT
TO GO.
HE'S A CANCER.
EVERYBODY UNANIMOUSLY THINKS
HE'S DISRESPECTFUL.
HE'S LAZY.
HE DOESN'T CONTRIBUTE, AND HE
RUFFLES FEATHERS FOR NO REASON.
TONIGHT'S VOTE IS AN OBVIOUS
VOTE FOR SHAMAR.
>> WOW!
THAT WAS A GOOD FEELING.
>> THAT WAS SO MUCH MORE FUN
THAN LAST TIME.
>> IT WAS WONDERFUL.
>> AND THE FISHING GEAR IS
GREAT.
>> FAVORITES WON THEIR FIRST
IMMUNITY, AND OUR REWARD WAS
FISHING GEAR.
PERFECT!
NET AND LURES SO WE CAN LINE
FISH IF WE WANT.
THERE WAS A HAWAIIAN SLING, SO
IT'S PRETTY EXCITING.
>> WE NEED TO GET SOME MORE
WOOD.
WE GOTTA GET THE FIRE BECAUSE
IT'S ASHES RIGHT NOW.
>> SO CORINNE IS THE DOMINATRIX.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
>> I'VE GOT YOUR NAME AS THE
ENFORCER.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> IN SEASON 22, SURVIVOR:
REDEMPTION ISLAND, I HAD AN
ORGANIZATION CALLED
"STEALTHR US."
WE HAVE NOW EXPANDED OUR
OPERATIONS HERE IN THE
Phillipines
AND I'VE GIVEN THEM EACH A
NAME.
THE NEWEST MEMBER OF
"STEALTH R US INC." IS THE
ENFORCER.
HIS CHALLENGE IS IF IT IS A MAN
OR WOMAN, HE PUT THEM OUT OF
COMMISSION TO WIN THE CHALLENGE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS GOING
THROUGH PHILLIP'S HEAD.
HE'S OUT HERE THINKING HE'S
RUNNING A CORPORATION, A SPY
CORPORATION.
AND HE'S REALLY GETTING
RIDICULOUS.
>> I CAN HAVE YOUR ATTENTION,
POLICE?
IT'S SO GREAT TO BE HERE AS THE
SPECIALIST, THE INTELLIGENCE
ATTACHE.
THE ENFORCER.
THE ELIMINATOR.
THE DOMINATRIX, AND TRUE GRIT.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> HERE TO SOLVE A MISSION THAT
FEW WOULD DARE TAKE ON-- TO BEAT
THE HECK OUT OF THE FANS.
>> BUT IF IT'S "STEALTH-R-US FOR
A FEW DAYS AND IT MAKES SOME
PEOPLE HAPPY, WHY NOT.
IF IT'S FOR THE REST OF THE
GAME, I'LL HANG MYSELF.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> THAT WAS COOL.
>> THIS SUCKS.
>> OH, WELL.
THERE'S NO FISH HERE ANYWAY.
( LAUGHS )
>> IT SUCKS TO LOSE, MAN.
WE ALL DID OUR BEST AND
OBVIOUSLY WANTED TO FREAKING
WIN.
>> THE WAY THEY DID IT WAS
PERFECT.
THEY HAD MUSCLE UP FRONT, MUSCLE
IN THE MIDDLE, MUSCLE AT THE
BACK, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> THAT'S THE THING.
WE WERE ALMOST READY TO START
AND WE DIDN'T KNOW WHO WAS DOING
WHAT?
THERE WASN'T ANYBODY OUT THERE
GOING, "HEY, EVERYBODY, WHAT ARE
WE DOING?"
>> EVERYBODY HAD THIS THING WHAT
THEY COULD AND COULDN'T DO.
IT IS WHAT IT IS, MAN.
>> SHAMAR, I'M GOING TO CALL YOU
OUT RIGHT NOW.
YOUR BEHAVIOR IS NOT ACCEPTABLE
FROM WHERE I COME FROM.
>> IT IS WHAT IT IS.
I DON'T HAVE AN OPINION SO YOU
AND YOUR FRIENDS YOU ALL CAN
TALK ABOUT WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
TALK ABOUT.
>> I JUST THINK THAT'S CHILDISH.
>> LET IT BE CHILDISH THEN.
>> WE HAD CHEMISTRY AND YOU
STARTED POUTING, "NO ONE WANTS
TO LISTEN TO SHAMAR."
>> LET IT BE CHILDISH.
>> I CAN'T STAND SHAMAR SO I
NEVER UNDERSTOOD WHY PEOPLE
WOULD THROW A CHALLENGE UNTIL I
LIVED WITH HIM FOR FIVE DAYS.
IT NEVER CROSSED MY MIND UNTIL I
LIVED WITH HIM.
I PRAY HE GOES HOME TONIGHT.
>> LISTEN, KEEP TALKING.
DO WHATEVER YOU DO.
>> WEATHER YOUR STRATEGY WAS
RIGHT, WRONG, OR INDIFFERENT,
YOUR BEHAVIOR IS NOT ACCEPTABLE
FROM WHERE I COME FROM.
>> IT IS WHAT IT IS.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO ABOUT
IT?
>> I'M GOING TO VOTE FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOOD THEN,
VOTE.
IT'S TOO EASY.
HE MADE A DRAMATIC SCENE.
IT CAME OUT OF NOWHERE, AND HE
DID IT IN FRONT FRONT OF
EVERYBODY, AND I FELT LIKE HE
KNOWS HIM AND THE THREE OTHER
PEOPLE IN HIS ALLIANCE ARE IN A
SHORT SITUATION SO HE TRIED TO
MAKE A SCENE TO MAKE ME LOOK BAD
SO PEOPLE WOULD WANT TO VOTE FOR
ME AND KEEP HIS ALLIANCE IN THE
GAME FOR ONE MORE CHALLENGE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING TO
ME ABOUT IT FOREVER?
LIKE YOU WEREN'T GOING TO VOTE
FOR ME BEFORE TODAY.
LIKE TODAY IS NOW, LIKE, VOTE
FOR SHAMAR KAY DAY.
DO I LOOK LIKE BOO-BOO THE FOOL.
YOU'RE TRYING TO MAKE IT ALL
ABOUT ME SO YOU CAN SWAY OTHER
PEOPLE'S OPINIONS BUT THAT'S ALL
GREAT, MAN.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS TONIGHT.
>> I'M GOING TO GET THIS FIRE
GOING AGAIN.
>> IS IT OUT?
>> ENOUGH IS ENOUGH WITH THAT
GUY.
>> I KNOW.
>> HOLY MOLY.
>> GO TALK ABOUT IT.
( LAUGHS )
>> WE WILL, SHAMAR.
>> SHUT UP!
STOP TALKING.
>> WE'VE GOT TO GO DO IT NOW
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T DO IT.
>> SHUT UP!
I CANNOT WAIT TO WRITE HIS NAME
DOWN.
I WANT HIM OUT OF HERE.
>> HE'S BEEN THE BIGGEST MOUTH.
>> AS I'M SAYING, I'M WITH YOU
GUYS, OBVIOUSLY, AND HOPE AND
ALLIE.
AND ONCE WE VOTE HIM OUT, WE
STILL HAVE--
>> THAT'S WHAT WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
>> IT'S TIME TO GO TO OUR FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND I HAVE
TWO CHOICES RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, MICHAEL AND I HAVE A
REALLY STRONG BOND, AND FITOLD
MICHAEL RIGHT NOW, HEY, MAN, I
THINK IT'S BETTER FOR US TO GO
WITH HOPE, ALLIE, EDDIE, AND
REYNOLD, THAT HE WOULD FOLLOW
SUIT.
>> WELL, I'VE SAID MY PIECE.
I'M STAYING OUT OF IT.
>> I'M NOT SAYING A WORD TO THE
DUDE UNTIL I WRITE HIS NAME
DOWN.
MY OTHER OPTION IS TO GO WITH
SHERRI, JULIA, SHAMAR, AND
LAURA.
I JUST NEED TO MAKE A DECISION
AND IT'S NOT GOING TO BE AN EASY
ONE.
>> THE QUESTION IS, IS IT SHAMAR
OR IS IT ONE OF THEM?
>> I THINK IT'S DEFINITELY ONE
OF THEM BECAUSE THEY'RE--
>> I DO, TOO.
>> HERE'S THE THING, EVEN IF WE
VOTE SHAMAR OUT, WE STILL HAVE A
5-4 ADVANTAGE, AND IF WE VOTE
OUT SHAMAR, EVERYBODY WILL BE
HAPPY, AND THE FOUR OF THEM,
EDDIE, REYNOLD, HOPE, AND ALLIE
WILL STILL THINK I'M WITH THEM
AND THEY HAVE A 5-4 ADVANTAGE.
>> SHAMAR RIGHT NOW IS PISSED
OFF.
HE KNOWS HIS NAME IS ON THE
BLOCK.
HE'S ONE REALIZES HE'S NOT GOING
HOME--
>> SHAMAR.
>> HE'LL CHILL OUT.
MATT SAID HE WAS ON THE FENCE
ABOUT VOTING OUT SHAMAR.
IT KIND OF GOT ME A LITTLE
WORRIED BECAUSE I WANT TO MAKE
SURE WHEN I GO TO SLEEP TONIGHT
THAT SHAMAR IS SAFE LAYING NEXT
TO ME.
>> DON'T SAY ANY WORD.
WHO WOULD YOU WITHOUT TALKING
WHO WOULD BE THE FIRST PERSON
YOU WOULD SAY?
>> I WOULD SAY ONE OF THE GIRLS.
I THINK ALLIE.
>> I'M TOTALLY COOL WITH THAT.
>> PERSONALLY, I THINK ALLIE'S A
STRATEGIC THREAT.
I THINK SHE'S THE ONLY ONE OUT
OF THE FOUR PRETTY PEOPLE THAT'S
REALLY THINKING.
>> SO IT'S ALLIE, UNLESS I HEAR
OTHERWISE.
>> IT'S ALLIE.
>> YOU KNOW, BEING A FAN OF THE
GAME, I KNOW THAT HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOLS ARE A PART OF
THE GAME.
AND I ASSUME THERE'S PROBABLY
ONE OUT HERE.
AND I DEFINITELY WANT IT.
THEY'RE USUALLY UNDER A TREE.
IT'S JUST A ROCK.
HOLY ( BLEEP ) 3 YOU'VE GOT TO
BE KIDDING ME!
ALL RIGHT, I REALLY-- I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR, LIKE, NOT THAT
LONG.
I WAS JUST THINKING WHERE WOULD
I HIDE AN IMMUNITY IDOL?
THIS IS ABSOLUTELY TOO CRAZY.
THIS IS TOO FREAKING CRAZY.
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU FOUND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THE IMMUNITY IDOL WILL KEEP YOU
SAFE FROM BEING VOTED OFF AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL."
I WANT TO TUCK THIS THING AWAY
MAKE SURE THAT NOBODY KNOWS I
HAVE IT.
AND THAT IS JUST ABSOLUTELY
FREAKING NUTS THEY JUST FOUND
THIS!
I HAVE FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, AND I'M, LIKE, REALLY
EXCITED RIGHT NOW, SO I'M TRYING
TO JUST, LIKE, CHECK MYSELF, BE
SMART ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW, NOT
WALK BACK TO CAMP WITH SOME
GIANT, STUPID GRIN ON MY FACE
AND A HUGE BULGE IN MY POCKET.
>> I'D RATHER DRINK THAN EAT,
PERSONALLY, BUT I'M JUST ONE
VOTE.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> A GIRL NEEDS HER FOOD.
( LAUGHS )
>> WE SHOULD JUST VOTE.
>> LET'S JUST VOTE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE MORE PEOPLE ARE
LEANING TOWARDS WATER.
>> OKAY, SO, RIGHT BEFORE WE'RE
ABOUT TO LEAVE FOR TRIBAL
COUNCIL, I SEE A BULGE IN
REYNOLD'S POCKET.
AND IT SEEMED LIKE THERE WAS
DEFINITELY SOMETHING IN IT.
AND WE ALL KNOW THAT THE ONLY
THING YOU WOULD PUT IN YOUR
POCKET BEFORE TRIBAL COUNCIL IS
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO I'M, LIKE, WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE?
IS THIS GOING TO MESS UP OUR
PLAN TO GET ALLIE OFF TONIGHT?
BECAUSE WE ALL KNOW THAT ALLIE
AND REYNOLD ARE REALLY CLOSE AND
THERE'S DEFINITELY A POSSIBILITY
THAT HE COULD PASS IT TO HER AND
SAVE HER BUTT, AND WE'RE TRYING
TO GET HER OFF.
AND IF HE PASSED THAT IDOL TO
ALLIE, THEN IT WOULD BE SHAMAR
GOING HOME AND NOT ALLIE, AND
THAT WOULD SCREW US OVER.
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT I'M THE
ONLY ONE THAT KNOWS.
BUT AT THIS POINT, THERE'S
REALLY NOT ENOUGH TIME TO TALK
TO THE REST OF OUR ALLIANCE.
SO I'M FREAKING OUT A LITTLE
BIT.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH.
APPROACH THE FLAME, DIP IT IN,
AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
THAT IS GOING TO BE THE CASE FOR
ONE OF YOU TONIGHT.
SO, MICHAEL, WHAT'S IT LIKE TO
FEND FOR YOURSELVES IN A
MILLION-DOLLAR GAME WITH PEOPLE
YOU PROBABLY WOULDN'T ACTUALLY
HAVE THAT MUCH IN COMMON?
>> WELL, MATT, AND SHERRI HAVE
FAMILIES IN COMMON.
THEY'RE MARRIED AND THEY HAVE
CHILDREN.
AND THEN THERE'S THE FOURSOME.
EDDIE AND HOPE AND ALLIE AND
REYNOLD.
>> Jeff: SO, ALLIE, DID YOU
GUYS JUST QUICKLY BECOME FAST
FRIEND THE FOUR OF YOU?
>> YEAH, I THINK IT'S KIND OF
THE SAME AGE GROUP.
WE HAVE THE SAME THINGS IN
COMMON.
WE WEREN'T EXCLUDING ANYBODY
OUT.
IT JUST KIND OF HAPPENED.
IT'S SOMETHING WE WOULD DO ON
THE OUTSIDE.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, WHAT'S YOUR
TAKE ON THE FOUR?
>> EDDIE AND HOPE SEEM LIKE A
COUPLE AND THESE TWO SEEM PART
OF THE FOURSOME.
>> Jeff: MATT, CONCERN YOU AT
ALL THAT THERE ARE FOUR PEOPLE
OPENLY SAYING,"WE'RE SIMILAR SO
WE HANG OUT A LOT TOGETHER ON
THE BEACH?"
>> NO.
LIKE, THEY SLEEP ON THE BEACH
TOGETHER.
MAYBE IT'S MORE COMFORTABLE FOR
THEM THAN THE SHELTER.
BUT I'M NOT, LIKE, MAJORLY
CONCERNED, NO.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, HOW HAS THIS
EXPERIENCE BEEN FOR YOU?
>> JEFF, I'M 300 POUNDS.
I'VE HAD, YOU KNOW, TWO SCOOPS
OF RICE AND THREE COCONUTS SINCE
I'VE BEEN HERE SO I'M KIND OF
JUST DRAINED A LITTLE BIT,
TRYING TO CONSERVE MY ENERGY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR
BACKGROUND, SHAMAR?
IS THIS THE TYPE OF ENVIRONMENT
YOU'RE USED TO OR IS THIS A
SHOCK TO YOU?
>> NO, I'VE DONE TWO TOURS IN
IRAQ WHERE I'VE BEEN IN, YOU
KNOW, DESERT SITUATIONS AND
SITUATIONS WHERE I DIDN'T HAVE
MUCH FOOD, AND THE ONLY
DIFFERENCE IS WE'VE HAD LEADERS
IN THE MARINE CORPS, AND A LOT
OF PEOPLE HERE ARE INDIVIDUALS,
AND IT'S NOT LIKE A TEAM EFFORT
ALL THE TIME.
YOU KNOW, NOBODY WANTS TO
LISTEN.
THEY WANT TO DO IT THEIR OWN
WAY, SO...
>> Jeff: MICHAEL, IS THAT WHAT
HAPPENED TODAY AT THE CHALLENGE?
WERE THERE TOO MANY VOICES?
>> YEAH, I QUE WHILE WE WERE
STRATEGIZING THAT WE WERE IN
TROUBLE.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE NINE PEOPLE GO
OUT IN THE FIELD WITHOUT ANYBODY
THINKING, WELL, WHOSE THE BEST
PITCHER?
WHO'S THE BEST CATCHER?
AND NOBODY MAKING THE DECISIONS.
AND THEN IT GOT HEAT, YOU KNOW.
>> Jeff: SO, REYNOLD, THIS WAS
GOING DOWN MOMENTS BEFORE AN
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> JEFF, I THINK TO WIN THESE
CHALLENGES YOU REAL NEED TO BE
ONE COHESIVE UNIT.
BUT I THINK PEOPLE GET
FRUSTRATED WITH SHAMAR'S
CRITIQUES OF HOW EVERYONE IS
DOING THEIR JOB AND SHAMAR KIND
OF SITS IN THE SHELTER ALL DAY
WHILE WE'RE ALL SWEATING AND
COVERED IN CUTS AND RASHES.
THAT'S WHERE THE FRUSTRATION
COMES.
FUP US TO THROW OUT, LIKE, 25
EXACT EXAMPLES WE'LL BE HERE ALL
NIGHT.
I'M NOT GOING TO WASTE YOUR
TIME, JEFF.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, YOU'RE
LAUGHING.
>> BECAUSE THEY COULDN'T GIVE
YOU 25 EXAMPLES RIGHT NOW, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
>> SHAMAR WAS IN THE HUT
YESTERDAY FOR 19 HOURS.
>> Jeff: 19 OF 24 HOURS?
>> YEAH, WHILE WE KEPT THE FIRE
BURNING, MADE DINNER, CUT
COCONUTS.
WE WANT SHAMAR TO COME OUT AND
HANG OUT BUT IT WASN'T
HAPPENING.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR WERE YOU IN
THE SHELTER FOR THE MAJORITY OF
THE DAY?
>> OH, YEAH, VERY MUCH SO.
I JUST FEEL LIKE I'M A GOOD
SCAPEGOAT.
I'VE BEEN THE OUTCAST A LITTLE
BIT FROM DAY ONE.
>> Jeff: BASED ON WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
>> I THINK I'M BIG AND LOUD,
JEFF.
I THINK I'M JUST A BIG, LOUD
GUY.
>> Jeff: LAURA, BEFORE WE GET
TO THE VOTE, WHAT DO YOU MAKE
ABOUT THIS?
>> WELL, COMING IN HERE TONIGHT,
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION THAT
WE WERE VOTING AS A FAMILY.
BUT I DID SEE SOMETHING ELSE GO
DOWN.
I SAW A BULGE FROM ONE POCKET.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU GOING TO SAY
WHO?
>> I WILL NOT SAY WHO.
NO.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU'RE LOOKING
DIRECTLY AT REYNOLD.
>> YEF, JEFF, I'M HOLDING THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL I FOUND ON
THE ISLAND.
APPARENTLY, MY PANT ARE TOO
TIGHT, AND YOU CAN SEE THE IDOL
IN MY POCKET, AND I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT WAS GOING TO GO DOWN
TONIGHT.
I STILL THOUGHT WE WERE A BIG,
HAPPY FAMILY AS WELL, AND I
THOUGHT WE WERE VOTING
UNANIMOUSLY.
>> THEN WHY BRING IT TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
IF YOU HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, WHY WOULD YOU NOT WRING IT
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL IS THAT NOT
"SURVIVOR 101."
JEFF, IT'S A SHAME BECAUSE I'M
PLAYING RIGHT NOW TO BEAT THE
FAVORITES.
>> Jeff:
>> Jeff: AND NOW YOU'RE
HOLDING THIS MASSIVE TARGET.
>> YEAH, THESE THINGS ARE
POCKETS FULL OF KRYPTONITE.
I MEAN, I'M GOING TO PLAY IT
TONIGHT AND THEN BE DONE WITH
IT.
SO GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
WHEN WE GO TO THE MERGE, THERE'S
NO MORE IDOL PARTY.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, THIS IS MAYBE
GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
NOW THERE'S SOMEBODY WITH AN
IDOL, AND HE WASN'T TELLING
EVERYBODY.
I MEAN, THIS THING HAS BLOWN UP.
>> I MEAN, HE DESERVES AN
ACADEMY AWARD.
HE TRIED TO THROW ME UNDER THE
BUS.
THE WHOLE FOUR THEY'VE BEEN
TRYING TO VILLINIZE ME FROM DAY
ONE AND THAT'S WHY I'VE TAKEN A
STEP BACK AND THE PEOPLE WHO
KNOW MY HEART ARE GOING TO VOTE
THE RIGHT WAY, AND THE PEOPLE
WHO DON'T LIKE ME, WILL VOTE,
YOU KNOW, AGAINST ME.
>> Jeff: SHERRI, THIS GAME IS
NOW COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
>> I AM JUST LIKE BLOWN AWAY OF
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
BUT I'M VOTING THE WAY I'M
SUPPOSED TO BE VOTING.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
I'M STICKING WITH MY VOTE.
MAYBE.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT HAS BEEN A
CRAZY INTRODUCTION TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL FOR THE FANS.
AND NOW IT IS TIME TO VETE.
EDDIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> THANK YOU FOR SERVING IN OUR
MILITARY.
I APPRECIATE IT.
OUT HERE, NOT SO MUCH.
>> YOU GOTTA GO BECAUSE FOUR IS
WAY TOO POWERFUL.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SHAMAR.
SHAMAR.
THAT'S THREE VOTES SHAMAR.
FOUR VOTES SHAMAR.
ALLIE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ALLIE, FOUR
VOTES SHAMAR.
ALLIE.
WE'RE TIED, FOUR VOTES ALEERK
FOUR VOTES SHAMAR.
ALLIE.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES ALLIE, FOUR
VOTES SHAMAR.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF "FANS
VERSUS FAVORITES" ALLIE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ALLIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: WELL, GIVEN THE
CRAZINESS OF YOUR FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, HERE'S SOMETHING WORTH
REMEMBER AGO IN ORDER TO WIN
THIS GAME, YOU HAVE TO GET TO
THE END.
IN ORDER TO GET TO THE END, YOU
HAVE TO BEAT THE FAVORITES.
IN ORDER TO BEAT THE FAVORITES,
YOU GOTTA GET IT TOGETHER.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
>> I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO SAID
THAT!
>> THE CAMP IS IN CHAOS.
>>
>> Jeff: SHAMAR IS MAKING CAMP
LIFE UNBEARABLE.
>> YOU ALL WROTE MY NAME DOWN.
>> HE WAS YELLING AT EVERYBODY.
>> Jeff: AND FOR THE FAVORITE
IT'S NOT MUCH BETTER.
>> I'LL PEE IN THE RICE.
I'LL PEE IN THE BEANS.
I'LL BURN THE SHELTER TO THE
GROUND.
>> I HAD A LOT MORE GAME TO
PLAY.
I WAS JUST SO FRUSTRATED.
BECAUSE THIS IS WHAT I WANTED
AND I JUST-- IT SUCKS.
I WANTED TO PLAY THIS GAME FOR
HALF MY LIFE.
I'VE WANTED THIS SINCE I WAS 11
YEARS OLD.
I'M MORTIFIED BEYOND WORDS THAT
I'M LEAVING SECOND.
I HAD SUCH A GOOD TIME PLAYING
THIS.
AARRGGHH! IT SUCKS!