>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AFTER THE MERGE, THE
POWER ALLIANCE HAD A 6-3
ADVANTAGE OVER MALCOLM, REYNOLD,
AND EDDIE.
BUT THEY WEREN'T THE ONLY ONES
STRUGGLING TO SURVIVE.
>> HOW CAN WE LIVE OFF OF WATER?
>> LACK OF FOOD AND INJURIES AND
STUFF, STUFF LIKE THAT SCARES
ME.
>> Jeff: AND AT TREE MAIL--
SURVIVORS FOUND A MUCH-NEED ED
GIFT.
>> WE SAW THERE WERE NINE
ENVELOPES SITTING THERE.
THE FOOD AUCTION IS UPON US.
>> Jeff: AT THE AUCTION-- NEXT
ITEM.
>> $500.
>> Jeff: SOLD "N."
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> MOST OF THE TRIBES FOCUSED ON
THEIR STOMACHS WHILE COCHRAN
FOCUSED ON THE GAME, VYING FOR
AN ADVANTAGE FOR THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS A SHOWDOWN.
AND IT WAS WORTH EVERY PENNY.
EDDIE IS OUT.
COCHRAN WINS IMMUNITY.
>> I'M READY TO TAKE OVER.
>> Jeff: BACK AT CAMP, SHERRY
AND ERIK WERE THE SWING VOTES,
BEING WOOED BY TWO ALLIANCES,
THE THE FORMER STEALTH "R" US-.
>> FOR ME, I HAVE TO KEEP
PLAYING BOTH SIDES.
>> Jeff: AND THE THREE AMIGOS.
>> AS OF THIS MOMENT RIGHT NOW,
I'M TORN OF WHO I'M GOING WITH.
>> Jeff: BUT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, EDDIE AND REYNOLD SAW
ANOTHER CHANCE TO CHANGE THE
GAME SLIP THROUGH THEIR FINGERS.
12 PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
MALCOLM, YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
MALCOLM, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
REYNOLD AND EDDIE, YOU'VE BEEN
ON THE OUTSIDE OF THIS GAME
SINCE DAY ONE.
BUT YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
EIGHT ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> WHOOO!
>> BIG VOTE.
>> AND YOU ME, EDDIE.
NOTHING'S CHANGED SINCE DAY ONE.
IT'S NOT THE THREE AMIGOS
ANYMORE.
MALCOLM'S GONE.
BUT THE GAME IS NOT OVER.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, I'M STILL
HERE.
I'M GOING TO KEEP FIGHTING.
TRUTHFULLY, IN MY MIND, I THINK
I'M CAPABLE OF WINNING FIVE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES IN A ROW.
>> LISTEN, I'M NOT SELLING
MYSELF SHORT.
WE DEFINITELY HAVE TO KEEP
PLAYING THE GAME AS HARD AS WE
POSSIBLY IT.
NO, YOU GUY GUYS -- YOU'RE STILL
HERE.
>> SINCE DAY, PRETTY MUCH TWO, I
HAVE BEEN PLAYING WITH MY BACK
AGAINST THE WALL ARE REYNOLD.
AND WE KNOW WE'RE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK EVERY TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
HOWEVER, WE'RE STILL HERE.
SO, YOU KNOW, JUST KEEP GOING.
KEEP ROLLING WITH THE PUNCHES.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN IN THIS
GAME.
>> WE NEED TO START THINKING
AHEAD.
BECAUSE REYNOLD GETTING TO THE
END, IF HE WOULD WIN EVERY ONE
IN A ROW-- I WANT HIM GONE.
>> THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> THE FANS ARE DESPERATE.
THEY'RE CORNERED.
THEY HAVE NO POWER.
THE POWER RESTS WITH THE
FAVORITES RIGHT NOW AND I WANT
TO TAKE AWAY AS MUCH POWER AND
SUCK IT UP FOR MYSELF AS
POSSIBLE BECAUSE I WANT TO TAKE
CONTROL OF THE GAME, AND I'LL DO
IT WITHOUT REMORSE.
I'LL DO IT WITHOUT ANY
RESERVATIONS.
IT'S SCARY THAT I'M SAYING THAT.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE TURNED INTO
SOMEBODY WHO WOULD SCARE MY
MOTHER IF SHE SAW ME.
I'M NOT THE LITTLE HARVARD NERD
WHO WAS TREMBLING IN THE BUSHES
LAST TIME.
>> TREE MAIL.
>> WE'VE GOT TREE MAIL,
EVERYBODY.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
>> "SHAKY FOOTING OR LOSS OF
CONTROL COULD PUT YOU OUT OF
THIS GAME.
LOSE FOCUS FOR EVEN A MOMENT,
AND TONIGHT YOU COULD LOSE YOUR
FLAME."
>> OH, MAN!
HERE WE GO!
>> SO ANOTHER TRIBAL.
THAT'S DEVASTATING.
I THOUGHT IT WAS A REWARD,
MAYBE.
TREE MAIL SHOCKED ME THIS
MORNING.
THIS GAME NEVER STOPS.
WE WOKE UP THIS MORNING AND
WE'RE THINKING OH, MAN I HOPE
THERE'S SOME COOL REWARD TODAY.
NOPE, IMMUNITY.
SO NOW WE HAVE TO BEAT REYNOLD
AND GO TO TRIBAL AND VOTE HIM
OFF BECAUSE REYNOLD IS A THREAT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: IT IS A WINDY DAY,
COCHRAN, BUT I WILL TAKE IT
BACK.
COCHRAN NOW EVEN SHIRTLESS.
IT'S A COMPLETE TRANSFORMATION.
THE GUY WHO WAS AFRAID TO TAKE
HIS SHIRT OFF JUST A FEW
YEARS AGO.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE ON A TRIANGULAR
PLATFORM IN THE WATER WITH YOUR
BARE FEET PERCHED ON VERY NARROW
FOOTHOLDS.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS, YOU WILL
MOVE UP, MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT TO BALANCE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, IS GUARANTEED A
ONE-IN-SEVEN SHO SHOT AT WINNING
THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, TODAY YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR REWARD.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: IF THE FORM OF
INFORMATION.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: FOR THIS GAME.
READ INTO THAT WHATEVER YOU
WANT.
>> I AM NUMBER ONE ON THE HIT
LIST, NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
I TO WIN OR I'M GOING HOME.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL DRAW FOR SPORT
AND GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY'S IN
POSITION.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS BALANCE ON
A VERY UNEVEN PLATFORM IN THE
WATER WITH THE WIND BLOWING.
THAT'S ALL.
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO STEP OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE--
>> OH, MAN!
THAT HAD TO BE FIRST?
>> Jeff: I HAVE A GIANT PLATE
FULL OF DONUTS.
>> Jeff: AND ICE COLD MILK.
>> I SO WANT THEM.
>> DP FOR IT, EDDIE.
>> WHAT KIND OF DONUTS ARE THEY?
>> Jeff: FRESH.
>> HEY, EDDIE, IF YOU DON'T DO
THIS, I'M GOING TO DO IT.
>> I'LL DO IT WITH YOU.
>> YOU'LL DO IT WITH ME?
>> REYNOLD, I'M GOING, BRO.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO, ERIK.
>> Jeff: ERR AND I CAN EDDIE
STEP OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
EDDIE'S BEEN ON THE OUTSIDE OF
THIS GAME SINCE DAY ONE, AND
HE'LL BE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT WITHOUT IMMUNITY,
WITHOUT ANY SECURITY.
SO, EDDIE, WAS IT WORTH IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW YET.
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> YEAH, I'LL FIND OUT.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD ALSO ON THE
OUTSIDE.
HE'S STILL OUT THERE FIGHTING.
GOTTA GET THROUGH COCHRAN.
HE'S BEEN ON A ROLL.
ALL RIGHT, WE ARE ABOUT TO MOVE
UP.
YOU CAN SIT DOWN FOR A SECOND.
YOU'RE GOING TO MOVE YOUR FEET
ONE STEP UP TO THE SECOND PERCH.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
HANDS UP.
AND WE ARE BACK ON.
IT'S GOING TO GET MORE
DIFFICULT.
AND A LITTLE MORE PAINFUL.
>> GEEZ.
>> Jeff: NEXT ITEM, THREE HOT
DOGS AND A SOFT DRINK.
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE IT.
I'M SORRY, GUYS.
I CAN'T-- LIKE, MY THIGHS ARE
ABOUT TO BURST.
THEY'RE TREMBLING, OKAY?
>> DO IT, COCHRAN.
>> Jeff: BOY YOU GOT NO LOVE
FROM ANY OF THEM.
NOBODY GAVE YOU THE SIGN OF
APPROVAL OR PERMISSION.
ENJOY.
YOU GAVE UP A SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
I HOPE IT WAS WORTH IT.
>> IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN A BIG
MISTAKE STEPPING OUT OF THE
GAME, BUT I COULDN'T LAST THAT
MUCH LONGER.
AS LONG AS ONE OF US WINS
IMMUNITY OORKT FINE.
THE GOAL IS TO KEEP IT OUT OF
THE HAND OF REYNOLD.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, UNSTABLE.
DAWN LIKE A SHARK, EYEING HER
PREY, JUST WATCHING.
HOPING HE WILL FALL.
>> I'M GOING NOWHERE!
>> BRING IT!
>> NOWHERE!
>> BRENDA, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE ARE
GOING TO MOVE UP TO THE NEXT
POSITION.
ARE YOU NOW GOING TO MOVE TO THE
TOP OF THE TRIANGULAR PLATFORM.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S COUNT IT IN.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
EVERYBODY HAS TRANSITIONED
NICELY, AND THIS CHALLENGE JUST
GOT A LOT MORE DIFFICULT.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GOOD.
>> Jeff: NO HAPPENED, NO BUTT.
>> USE YOUR ARMS!
>> Jeff: THIS IS IT.
THERE ARE NO MORE TRANSITIONS.
WE PLAY IT OUT FROM HERE.
NICE SAVE.
DAWN WITH A VERY CLOSE CALL.
>> SHERRY, SHAKING ALL OVER, BUT
STILL THERE.
>> YES, SHERRY!
SHERRY, YOU CAN DO IT.
>> Jeff: BICK GUST OF WIND
COMING UP.
>> SON OF A --
>> DAWN FALLS OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE, AND WE ARE DOWN TO
FOUR.
SHERRI CANNOT HOLD ON ANY
LONGER.
SHERRI FALLS OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
>> GOOD JOB, SHERRI!
>> Jeff: NOW WE ARE DOWN TO
THREE-- ANDREA AND BRENDA AND
REYNOLD.
THE WIND IS NOW PROVING TO BE
THE BIGGEST ADVERSARY.
VERY STRONG.
REYNOLD WITH A HUGE RECOVERY.
>> WOW.
>> WAY TO GO, REYNOLD.
>> THAT WAS WILD!
>> Jeff: HE IS NOT GOING TO GO
DOWN EASY, LADIES.
>> OH!
OH!
>> Jeff: NICE SAVE BY BRENDA.
>> OH!
OH!
>> Jeff: ANDREA WITH A NICE
LITTLE SAVE.
CAN SNEAK UP OUT OF NOWHERE
REYNOLD STRUGGLING.
ANOTHER INCREDIBLE RECOVERY!
>> GOOD JOB, REYNOLD.
>> NO WAY!
>> Jeff: WOW!
KEEP WORKING.
EVERYBODY STAY FOCUSED.
>> HANG IN THERE, GIRLS!
>> Jeff: THIS TIME, REYNOLD
FALLS IN, AND IMMEDIATELY BRENDA
IS SMILING.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO STAY?
HE'S GONE.
>> OKAY,IMENT TO STAY.
I'LL SHARE THE CLUE WITH YOU, IF
YOU JUMP OFF.
>> Jeff: ONE PERSON IS WALKING
OUT OF HERE WITH IMMUNITY.
IT WILL NOT BE REYNOLD.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO ANDREA AND
BRENDA.
WILL A DEAL BE STRUCK?
>> IF YOU BEAT ME, I'LL BE SUPER
HAPPY WITH YOU.
BUT I'D RATHER YOU BEAT ME THEN
JUMP OFF.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED OR SOMETHING?
>> I JUST HAVEN'T WON ONE YET.
I JUST KIND OF WANT TO STICK IT
OUT.
YOU KNOW THAT YOU'RE SAFE, TOO?
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: PERCHED THREE HOURS.
>> GOOD JOB!
MAKE A DEAL!
>> WANT TO SCREW IT UP OR
SOMETHING?
>> WE COULD DO ONE FOOT.
>> Jeff: IF YOU GUYS WANT TO
TAKE IT TO THE NEXT LEVEL AND
DECIDE WHAT THE FOURTH STAGE IS.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> IF WE CAN LIFT UP OUR LEFT
LEG, THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
>> LIFT UP YOUR LEFT LEG.
>> Jeff: THIS IS YOUR RULE,
NOT MINE.
I'LL COUNT YOU IN.
FIVE, FOUR THREE, TWO, ONE.
LIFT.
HISTORIC.
THEY MADE THEIR OWN RULES UP TO
FINISH OUT THIS CHALLENGE.
BRENDA FALLS IN FIRST.
ANDREA WINS IMMUNITY!
( APPLAUSE )
AND REWARD IN THE FORM OF
INFORMATION IN THIS GAME!
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: ANDREA, SAFE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL,
GUARANTEED A ONE-IN-SEVEN SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION TO IMMUNITY, YOU
HAVE INFORMATION IN THIS GAME.
IT IS YOURS TO DO WITH WHATEVER
YOU WANT.
EVERYBODY ELSE, AFTER 31 DAYS,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEAL YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> IT'S EXCITING BECAUSE REYNOLD
DIDN'T WIN IMMUNITY, SO WE CAN
SPLIT THE VOTE.
WE'RE GOOD.
ONE OF THEM IS GOING HOME.
THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE DID YOU HANG, THIS
COCHRAN?
>> I PUT IT RIGHT UP TOP THERE.
>> IT WAS A MUST WIN FOR
PERSONAL IMMUNITY, DIDN'T GET
IT.
IT'S BASICALLY REYNOLD'S EULOGY
RIGHT NOW, BUT IF THEY'RE SMART,
BOOM, NOW IS THE TIME TO STRIKE
AND BLINDSIDE, SOMEONE WHO COULD
REALLY WIN THIS GAME.
THERE ARE THINGS THEY COULD
STILL DO STRATEGICALLY,
UNFORTUNATELY, I'M NOT THE
CONDUCTOR RIGHT NOW.
>> HAVE FUN WITH THE
INFORMATION.
>> I THOUGHT AFTER REYNOLD
DROPPED OUT, I'D SAY, YOU KNOW,
BRENDA, YOU WON THE LAST
IMMUNITY, COULD I JUST HAVE THIS
ONE?
BUT SHE STOOD ON THAT PERCH FOR
HOURS.
SHE REALLY PROVED THAT SHE'S A
BIG THREAT, SO THERE'S A HUGE
PART OF ME THAT REGRETD
PROMISING TO SHARE THE NOTE WITH
BRENDA.
WHICH I FOUND OUT IT WAS CLIEWT
TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AT
THAT POINT, I DIDN'T WANT TO BE
SUSPICIOUS SO I TOLD MY WHOLE
ALLIANCE. MOST IMPORTANT THING
ABOUT TODAY IS THE IDOL IS NOT
IN REYNOLD'S OR EDDIE'S HANDS.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
>> RIGHT WHERE ERIK IS SITTING,
RIGHT?
>> I COME FROM A FAMILY OF
DIGGERS.
>> GUYS?
>> GUYS, GUYS, GUYS.
>> NO WAY!
>> IT'S RIGHT THERE.
>> WE GOT IT.
>> ERIK FINDS THE IDOL, AND I'M
THINKING MAN TASK.
I CAN PROBABLY TELL HIM WHAT TO
DO WITH THE IDOL, HE'LL DO IT,
AND BEFORE I HAVE A CHANCE TO
START CELEBRATING HE'S ALREADY
HANDING THE IDOL OVER TO ANDREA.
DOES HE LEARN NOTHING.
>> THANK YOU, ANDREA.
>> THAT GETS US THROUGH THE NEXT
VOTE, RIGHT.
>> I REALLY WANT TO GET REYNOLD
OUT, BUT I'M STILL CONTEMPLATING
IF WE THROW A BLINDSIDE IN THERE
BECAUSE IT WILL BE AN END GAME
TO GET OUT A STRATEGIC THREAT
NOW WHEN THEY DON'T SEE IT
SOME BLINDSIDES NEED TO HAPPEN
BEFORE IT HAPPENS TO ME.
>> IF IT'S WATER CHALLENGES
SHE'S GOT IT.
SHE HASN'T PISSED ANYONE OFF.
>> I THINK TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AND THE FIGHT
DEMONSTRATED BY PLAYERS LIKE
ANDREA AND BRENDA MARKED
POSSIBLY THE BEGINNING OF THE
END FOR THE ALLIANCE OF SIX.
THERE ARE STILL TWO EASY VOTES
IN REYNOLD AND EDDIE.
WE CAN SPLIT THE VOTES BETWEEN
OF TWO OF THEM, AND ONE WILL BE
SENT PACKING.
AND YET WE SEE THE
SELF-INTERESTED DESIRE BUBBLING
TO THE SURFACE AND PEOPLE ARE
PLAYING FOR THE END GAME FOR
THEIR OWN VICTORY INSTEAD OF A
GROUP VICTORY.
>> MAYBE SHE'S ON BOARD AND WILL
GO ALONG WITH THE BRENDA VOTE.
I THINK THAT WOULD BE SO MUCH
MORE EXCITING EVERYONE WOULD
THINK IT WAS REYNOLD.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT GOOD.
>> ANDREA IS A SMART PLAYER, AND
ANDREA, LIKE ME, IS THINKING
WELL BEYOND THE SIX, AND IT'S
ANDREA'S OPINION THAT THE RIGHT
BIG MOVE TO MAKE TO TO BLINDED
SIDE BRENDA.
THIS GAME IS ALL ABOUT TIMING.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO THE BIGGEST
THREAT IS.
I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE BRENDA IS A
THREAT.
BUT I WANT REYNOLD GONE.
HE'S DISRUPTIVE FOR MY BRAIN.
>> I THINK IT'S BRENDA.
I THINK SHE'S THE BIGGEST THREAT
TO US.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE SOMEONE
LIKE THAT WIN, BUT THEY WOULD.
>> THIS IS THE LONGEST I'VE BEEN
IN THE GAME.
TO BE THIS CLOSE MAKES ME FEEL
LIKE THESE DECISIONS ARE GOING
TO BE THE REALLY CRITICAL ONES
FOR ME.
THE BEST THING FOR THE ALLIANCE
WOULD BE TO HAVE PROBABLY EDDIE
OR REYNOLD GO NEXT.
BUT IT'S DEFINITELY AN OPTION TO
BLINDSIDE BRENDA.
THE BIGGEST OBSTACLE FOR ME IS
NOT HAVING AN OPPONENT OUT HERE.
THE BIGGEST OBSTACLE FOR ME HAS
BEEN MY MIND.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
MIKE.
PHILLIP.
AND MALCOLM, VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT TODAY'S
IMMUNITY AND REWARD CHALLENGE.
EDDIE AND ERIK OPT OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE EARLY ON FOR FOOD.
WHAT WAS YOUR RATIONALE, EDDIE,
GIVEN THAT YOU AND REYNOLD HAVE
BEEN ON THE OUTSIDE FOR A LONG
TIME?
>> TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST, I
KNEW I WASN'T GOING TO BE ABLE
TO STAND ON THAT THING FOR MORE
THAN MAYBE AN HOUR TOPS.
SO I JUMPED TO EAT, PRETTY MUCH.
AND I KIND OF SACRIFICED SOME
SECURITY AND SELF PRIDE FOR A
FEW DONUTS.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: SO THEN COCHRAN DROPS
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
THEN DAWN AND SHERRI, AND THAT
LEAVES US WITH BRENDA, ANDREA,
AND REYNOLD.
SO ONCE REYNOLD FALLS OUT, WHY
DID YOU TWO STAY UP THERE
ANOTHER TWO, THREE HOURS?
WHY, IF THERE'S SUCH A TIGHT
BOND OF SIX, DIDN'T YOU JUST
MAKE A DEAL AND SAY YOU TAKE IT,
I'VE HAD IT, LET'S GO?
>> WHEN DO YOU GET THE
OPPORTUNITY TO TEST YOURSELF
LIKE THAT.
IT WASN'T NECESSARILY A LOT OF
FUN, BUT I'M HAPPY THAT I GOT
BEAT VERSUS THEY JUMPED OFF.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, IT IS A
LITTLE CURIOUS THAT THEY DON'T
JUST MAKE A DEAL AND GET DOWN IF
THEY'RE SO TIGHT.
IS THERE ANY PART OF YOU
THINKING MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
TO IT, AND MAYBE THERE'S AN
OPENING FOR ME SOMEWHERE?
>> YEAH, I'M A GUY EVERYONE
ASSUMES IS GOING TO BE HOME, BUT
I COULD BE A GREAT INSTRUMENT.
ANY MOVES YOU WANT TO MAKE.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, REYNOLD'S
APPROACH TO COME IN AND TRY AND
STIR IT UP IS VALID IN ONE
SENSE.
IT'S TIMING.
HE'S SAYING IF NOW'S THE TIME TO
MAKE A MOVE, USE ME.
>> I MEAN, IT IS TIMING.
IF YOU'RE TOO LATE, THAT MEANS
YOU'RE GOING TO BE VOTED OFF.
IT'S ABOUT MAKE THE MOVE THE
SECOND A MOVE IS ABOUT TO BE
MADE AGAINST YOU.
AND IT TAKES A LOT OF
SELF-AWARENESS TO BE ABLE TO
PULL OFF SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> Jeff: AND, DAWN, NO
COMFORTABLE YOU FEEL, IT'S
POSSIBLE IT'S YOU THAT'S ON THE
OUTSIDE TONIGHT.
>> ALWAYS, ALWAYS.
THE LONGER I PLAY THIS TIME
AND PLAY BOTH SIDES, THE HARDER
IT IS FOR ME TO TRUST PEOPLE AT
ALL BECAUSE I KNOW I'M NOT
TRUSTWORTHY AT TIMES, OR HAVEN'T
BEEN.
>> Jeff: WHAT DAWN HAS SAID IS
ONE OF THE MOST HONEST THINGS
SOMEBODY HAS SAID AT TRIBAL.
YOUR PARANOIA COMES FROM
SOMETIMES YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT
TRUSTWORTHY.
>> WHEN YOU KNOW YOU CAN LIE AND
DECEIVE PEOPLE, YOU KNOW THE
PEOPLE YOU'RE PLAYING WITH CAN
DO THE SAME THING TO YOU.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN IF YOU THINK
YOUR ALLIANCE IS FLIPPING ON YOU
AT EVERY SECOND.
>> Jeff: HAVE YOU THOUGHT THAT
ABOUT YOUR ALLIANCE?
>> OH, YEAH.
TALL TAKES IS FOR ONE PERSON TO
FLIP OVER AND YOU'RE GONE.
OFF OF A SUDDEN, THE NUMBERS
DWINDLING, AND YOU REALIZE THERE
ARE A LOT OF CAPABLE PEOPLE
AROUND ME.
>> Jeff: EDDIE, THE BEST THING
YOU CAN HEAR, THEY'RE
QUESTIONING PEOPLE IN THEIR OWN
SIX.
>> IF YOU LOOK AT THESE SIKS,
THEY'RE ALL MAJOR PLAYERS.
IT'S LIKE WOW.
WHO IS GOING TO VOTE FOR WHO?
I CAN MAYBE SQUEEZE MYSELF IN
HERE.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, WE'RE RIGHT
ON THE CUSP OF THAT PLACE WHERE
YOU'RE THINKING WHO DO I WANT
LEFT IN THAT GAME?
REYNOLD AND EDDIE, THEIR BACKS
ARE AGAINST THE WALL THEY ARE
VOTES.
IF YOU KEEP THEM AROUND YOU CAN
GET RID OF A DAWN, COCHRAN,
BRENDA, ERIK.
>> Jeff: OR ANDREA.
>> OR ANDREA.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
ERIK YOU'RE UP.
>> I THINK THINGS WOULD HAVE
GONE A LOT BETTER FOR YOU IF YOU
HAD BEEN A LITTLE BIT MORE
HUMBLE IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, AND YOU WANT TO
USE IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO
DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ERIK.
SHERRI.
RENOLD.
EDDIE.
REYNOLD.
TWO VOTES REYNOLD, ONE VOTE FOR
ERIK, SHERRI, AND EDDIE.
EDDIE.
TWO VOTES EDDIE.
REYNOLD.
THAT'S THREE VOTES REYNOLD, TWO
VOTES EDDIE, ONE VOTE LEFT.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
REYNOLD.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD LUCK, DUDE.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
>> IT'S BEEN A BLAST YOU GUYS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
>> SEE YOU, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: WELL, WE ARE DOWN TO
ONE AMIGO LEFT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> HERE I AM.
ADIOS.
I PUT MY TRUST IN A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT WASN'T RECIPRICATED
AND I HAD NO MORE RABBITS I
COULD PULL OUT OF MY HAT, NO
MORE IMMUNITY IDOLS.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING FOR
SURE.
I HAD THE TIME OF MY LIFE.
>> YEAH.
>> THERE'S ONLY SEVEN OF US
LEFT.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> IT FINALLY FEELS LIKE A SMALL
GROUP NOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S SO WEIRD.
>> THE GUNSLINGERS TAKE OUT
ANOTHER VICTIM.
>> FINALLY, REYNOLD WENT HOME,
WHICH IS A HUGE RELIEF.
AND NOW WE'RE AT FINAL SEVEN.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WE DIDN'T MAKE THE BIG MOVE
TONIGHT, BUT NOW I'M THINKING
ABOUT WHAT'S NEXT.
AND THE OBVIOUS IS WHY TONIGHT
WE BLINDSIDE SOMEBODY WHEN THEY
DON'T SEE IT COMING AND THIS IS
GOING TO COME DOWN WHO WE DECIDE
IS THE BIGGER THREAT.
WE HAVE TO REMEMBER IT'S A GAME
FOR A MILLION DOLLARS.
AND IF WE DON'T DO IT, THEY'RE
GOING TO DO IT TO US.
IT HAS TO BE DAWN OR BRENDA.
I CAN'T DECIDE BETWEEN THEM.
BRENDA LIKE, CHALLENGES, SHE'S
REALLY STRONG, AND SHE HASN'T
PISSED ANYBODY OFF.
DAWN, YOU KNOW, SHE'LL TURN ON
ANYBODY AT ANY SECOND.
I COWL SEE HER BACKSTAB ME, YOU,
ANYBODY,UN.
I THINK MAYBE, UM, "B" SHOULD GO
FIRST, IF WE HAVE A CHOICE.
>> I'M ALL ABOUT MAKING BIG
MOVES, AND ANDREA, TO HER CREDIT
IS WILLING TO MAKE A BIG MOVE,
BUT IT'S A BIG MOVE I DON'T
AGREE WITH.
ONCE AGAIN SHE'S TALKING ABOUT
TAKING OUT BRENDA, AND DAWN, WHO
IS PROBABLY MY CLOSEST ALLY IN
THE GAME.
>> EDDIE.
>> HE REALLY SHOULD BE THE NEXT
TARGET.
>> HE NEEDS TO GO.
>> PERIOD.
>> BUT THIS IS WHAT I WAS
THINKING--
>> .
>> COCHRAN TOLD ME THAT ANDREA
WANTS TO BLINDSIDE ME OR DAWN
AND THAT SHOWS JUST HOW
UNTRUSTWORTHY SHE IS, SO NOW I
WANT ANDREA OUT OF THE GAME
BECAUSE SHE WANTS ME OUT OF THE
GAME.
IT WOULD ALMOST BE EASIER TO GET
RID OF ANDREA BEFORE EDDIE.
>> I'M JUST SO SCARED OF HER
HAVING THE IDOL.
>> WORST-CASE SCENARIO, WE COULD
ALL AS A GROUP TOGETHER
BLIEPPEDSIDE HER.
SHERRI'S WITH US 100%.
>> YOU THINK ERIK WILL BE COOL
WITH THIS?
>> PROBABLY.
>> ANDREA I THINK IS ONE OF THE
FEW REMAINING INDEPENDENT
THINKERS, AND THAT'S A DANGEROUS
THING, AND THE TIME TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE IS RAPIDLY APPROACHING.
SO IF ANDREA DOESN'T WIN THE
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE AND SHE
DOESN'T PLAY THE IDOL, SHE MIGHT
BE GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: GIVE IT UP, ANDREA.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'LL
PUSH A BUOY THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES TO A POST HOLDING A
KEY.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE KEY, YOU'LL
UNLOCK A CHEST, CONTAINING
LADDER RUNGS AND USE THEM TO
COMPLETE A LADDER PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO COMPLETE THEIR
LADDER AND CLIMB TO THE TOP AND
RAISE THEIR FLAG AND WINS
IMMUNITY, GAWSHTED A ONE-IN-SIX
SHOT OF WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
AFTER 33 DAYS OUT HERE, SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO!
FOR IMMUNITY!
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU'VE GOT TO PUSH YOUR BOWIE
THROUGH THE ROPE OBSTACLE.
ROPE MANAGEMENT IS KEY.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED SLACK AT
CERTAIN TIMES.
BRENDA OFF TOW A VERY FAST
START.
ERIK OFF TO A QUICK START.
EDDIE'S IN THIS.
COCHRAN'S IN IT.
SHERRI FALLING BEHIND QUICKLY.
IT IS BRENDA AND ERIK RIGHT NOW
IN THE LEAD.
ERIK OUT FIRST.
START WORKING ON THOSE KNOTS.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO UNTIE A KEY.
BRENDA'S GETTING HUNG UP.
COCHRAN IS THROUGH SECOND.
HERE COMES DAWN AND ANDREA NOW.
THERE GOES BRENDA!
EDDIE'S IN IT.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR KEY
EXCEPT SHERRI.
RIP THROUGH THOSE KNOTS!
LET'S GO!
ONCE YOU GET THROUGH IT, IT WILL
RELEASE A KEY.
THAT'S THE KEY YOU NEED TO
OPPONENT THE CHEST.
SHERRI NOW GETTING IN ON IT.
ANDREA DOING A GREAT JOB ON THE
KNOTS.
EDDIE'S FLYING THROUGH THE
ERIK IS THROUGH FIRST FROM THIS
STAGE AS WELL.
NOW ANDREA'S IN IT.
THERE GOES EDDIE.
BRENDA VERY CLOSE.
BRENDA IS FREE NOW.
COCHRAN, DAWN, AND SHERRI STILL
WORKING ON THEIR KNOTS, QUICKLY
FALLING OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
THIS IS A LADDER PUZZLE.
EVERY PIECE IS UNIQUE AND ONLY
GOES IN ONE SPOT AND YOU HAVE TO
BUILD FROM THE BOTTOM TO THE
TOP.
DAWN HAS HER KEY.
SHE'S UP.
ANDREA HAS HER FIRST.
BRENDA HAS HER FIRST.
SHERRI HAS HER KEY, SHE'S
WORKING.
THERE'S COCHRAN, THE LAST ONE,
EVERYBODY NOW WORKING ON THEIR
LADDER.
BRENDA WITH HER SECOND.
ERIK STILL TRYING TO FIND HIS
FIRST.
RIGHT NOW, IT IS ANDREA AND
BRENDA.
ANDREA WOULD LIKE TO WIN
IMMUNITY AGAIN.
YOU WANT TO BE SAFE TONIGHT.
YOU CANNOT RISK IT.
THERE'S ONLY SEVEN PEOPLE LEFT.
ERIK WITH HIS FIRST PIECE.
EDDIE'S GOT HIS FIRST PIECE.
COCHRAN NOW GETTING IN ON IT.
HE'S GOT TWO.
BRENDA WITH HER THIRD LADDER
RUNG.
ERIK WITH HIS SECOND.
EDDIE TRYING TO FIND HIS SECOND.
SHERRI STRUGGLING.
ERIK WITH THREE PIECES.
RIGHT NOW, IT IS ERIK AND
BRENDA.
ERIK WITH HIS FOURTH.
ANDREA STILL STUCK BACK AT ONE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING!
>> Jeff: SHE CANNOT FIND THE
SECOND RUNG.
ERIK FLYING THROUGH THIS.
ERIK NOW WITH SIX LADDER RUNGS.
BRENDA STILL WORKING ON HER
FOURTH.
'RIERIK WITH HIS SEVENTH.
BRENDA WITH HER FOURTH.
ERIK HAS TWO LEFT.
EDDIE STILL STRUGGLING.
IT IS A BLOWOUT.
ERIK HAS ONE RUNG LEFT.
THIS WILL DO IT.
ERIK WINS IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A
SPOT IN THE FINAL SIX!
>> WHOOO!
>> WHAT? !
>> GOOD JOB, ERIK.
>> Jeff: ERIK, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
GOOD JOB, ERIK.
>> Jeff: ERIK WINS IMMUNITY.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THE LAST TIME YOU HAD
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE IN THIS
GAME WAS THE FIRST TIME YOU
PLAYED, AND YOU GAVE IT AWAY AND
WERE VOTED OUT.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE THAT HAPPENS
TONIGHT?
>> I'M WAY TOO SCARED TO DO THAT
THIS TIME, WAY TOO SCARED.
>> Jeff: ERIK WITH THIS AROUND
HIS NECK WILL BE SAFE AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 33
VERY TOUGH DAYS, SOMEBODY GOING
HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANKS.
>> ERIK, YOU WERE SO FAST.
THEY WERE EASY PIECES TO
FIND.
>> I WAS PUTTING THEM IN, IN THE
WRONG WAY AT FIRST.
>> THE CHALLENGE WAS RIGHT UP MY
ALLEY.
I MEAN, I KILLED IT, AND WON
IMMUNITY.
AND THIS TIME AROUND, I'VE
LEARNED FROM MISTAKES I MADE IN
THE PAST.
SO THIS IS NOT ANY KIND OF MORAL
DECISION FOR ME TO MAKE WHETHER
OR NOT TO GIVE IT TO SOMEONE
ELSE OR KEEP IT.
THIS IS A SAFETY BLANK THAT THE
CAN GET ME FARTHER IN THIS GAME.
( THUNDER )
>> BRENDA MADE MY JOB TONIGHT
PRETTY EASY BY BEING A CHALLENGE
THREAT.
SO I WANTED BRENDA OUT.
I TALKED TO EVERYBODY, AND NOW
SHE'S GOING.
AND I FEEL BAD FOR THE KID
BECAUSE GOING BACK TO MY FIRST
SEASON, I FELT COMPLETELY
COMFORTABLE, AND THEN, BAM, I
WAS BLINDSIDED.
SO I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE
LIED TO.
I HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I'M GOING TO BRING IT TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IF ALL OF A SUDDEN I FEEL
PARANOID, I WOULD PLAY IT.
BUT RIGHT NOW, IT DOES SEEM LIKE
MY DUCKS ARE IN A ROW, AND IT'S
GOING TO WORK OUT.
>> THEY'RE ALL DOWN.
>> IT'S BRENDA.
>> IT WAS SUPPOSE TO BE YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> I HAVE BEEN TRICKED, FOOLED,
AND PRETTY MUCH EVERY OTHER
ADJECTIVE BEFORE EVERY TRIBAL
COUNCIL, BUT I FEEL A LITTLE BIT
DIFFERENTLY TONIGHT.
ANDREA TOLD ME EVERYBODY IS
GOING TO BLINDSIDE BRENDA AND
THERE IS NO REASON TO LIE TO ME.
THEY KNOW I DON'T HAVE A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, SO FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN 33 DAYS I THINK I'M
GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL WITH AN
IDEA OF WHO WE'RE VOTING FOR AND
WHO'S GOING HOME.
>> WORST-CASE SCENARIO, EDDIE,
LET'S SAY.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
MENTION EDDIE'S NAME FOR THE
PAST 10 DAYS WITHOUT ANDREA
SAYING, EDDIE IS HARMLESS.
I CONTROL HIS VOTE.
AND NOW IT ALL MAKES SENSE, SHE
WANTS TO GO TO THE FINAL 3 WITH
HIM.
>> SHE'S GOING TO HAVE TO GO,
CORCORAN.
>> I KNOW.
WHETHER IT'S PERSONAL, WHETHER
IT'S STRATEGIC, I DON'T KNOW,
BUT THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS,
EDDIE IS MOVING UP ON ANDREA'S
PRIORITY LIST SO I'M WORRIED I'M
GOING TO BE REPLACED BY EDDIE.
I ADMIRE ANDREA FOR VAGUE GAME
PLAN.
BUT THAT PLAN DOESN'T INCLUDE
ME.
I WANT TO BE A PART OF
EVERYBODY'S PLAN, AND IF I'M NOT
A PART OF YOUR PLAN, ANDREA,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE A PART OF
MINE.
>> I KNOW THAT ANDREA WANTS TO
BLINDED SIDE ME SO THIS IS A
VERY TRICKY VOTE.
IT'S A LEAP OF FAITH.
I'M WRITING DOWN ANDREA AND HOPE
I DON'T GO HOME.
SO I'M IN HUGE DANGER.
BUT THE PLAN'S ALREADY BEEN
ENACTED.
I JUST HAVE TO JUST LET IT RIDE.
>> GOTCHA.
>> ONCE AGAIN, I HAVE TO TRUST
ERIK, THE ICE CREAM SCOOPER WHO
GAVE UP HIS IDOL AND WAS
PROMPTLY VOTED OUT, AND THAT'S
SCARY.
>> I'M SO HAPPY THAT YOU WON.
TONIGHT, YOU KNOW IT'S BRENDA.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU WIN EVERY
CHALLENGE, I WOULD LOVE TO GO TO
THE END WITH YOU.
>> THE OTHER THING SWE HAVE THE
HIDDEN IDOL.
O IT'S EVEN MORE CONTROL.
>> ANDREA CAME UP TO ME PRETTY
MUMP SAID SHE WANTS TO TAKE ME
ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
I PRETTY MUCH BELIEVE IT.
SO I HAVE AN IN WITH BOTH
ALLIANCES AT THIS POINT.
BOTH ALLIANCES THINK I'M ON
THEIR SIDE.
BUT COCHRAN HASN'T PROMISED ME
FINAL THREE, SO IF THEY SPLIT
THE VOTE, I COULD TOTALLY SHAKE
THINGS UP.
I FEEL SO MUCH CALMER TODAY.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S THE FIRST TIME I PLAYED
THE GAME.
I WAS PRETTY MUCH AT THE MERCY
OF WHAT EVERYBODY ELSE WANTED TO
DO.
THIS TIME AROUND IT'S VERY
DIFFERENT.
I'M ACTUALLY IN CONTROL OF THE
GAME TFEELS LIKE.
AND I'M GOING TO DO WHATEVER IS
BEST FOR ME.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
MICHAEL.
PHILLIP.
MALCOLM.
AND REYNOLD, VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, EDDIE, YOU'RE THE LAST ONE
OUTSIDE OF THE GROUP OF SIX.
IF THEY WANT TO GET RID OF YOU,
IT'S EASY.
BUT YOU COULD ARGUE, IF SOMEBODY
WANTS TO MAKE A MOVE, WE CAN
ALWAYS GET RID OF EDDIE AT THE
NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE
YOU'LL STILL BE IN THE SAME
SPOT, ON THE OUTSIDE.
>> ABSOLUTE.
COCHRAN TALKS A LOT ABOUT TIMING
AND IT'S EVERYTHING IN THIS
GAME.
IF THE BLINDSIDE WAS TO HAPPEN,
TONIGHT WOULD BE THE PERFECT
NIGHT FOR IT.
>> Jeff: BRENDA, IF YOU DON'T
MAKE A BIG MOVE TONIGHT, WHAT
HAPPENS TOMORROW?
>> WELL, I MEAN, WE'RE NOT-- I
MEAN, SOMETHING'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO START LYING
TO EACH OTHER AND HURTING PEOPLE
AND ALL THAT STUFF THAT COMES
WITH "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: SHERRI, DO YOU
BELIEVE PEOPLE ARE NOT LYING TO
EACH, RIGHT NOW WITHIN THE SIX?
>> I DEFINITELY BELIEVE PEOPLE
ARE LYING TO EACH GLRG DO YOU
THINK YOU'VE BEEN LIED TO?
>> I'M PRETTY SURE I'VE BEEN
LIED TO.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, DO YOU THINK
YOU'VE BEEN LIED TOW BY SOMEBODY
WITHIN THE SIX?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
MULTIPLE PEOPLE HAVE TOLD MY MEE
THEY INTEND TO DO TO THENT WITH
ME AND THEY DON'T INTEND TO GO
TO THE END WITH ME.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, WHEN YOU HEAR
COCHRAN SAY, NOT ONLY HAVE
PEOPLE PROMISED ME, BUT I'VE
PROBABLY PROMISED OTHERS.
HE'S SAYING NOT ALL THE THINGS
I'VE SAID ARE NECESSARILY TRUE.
>> EXACTLY, AND THAT MAKES ME
NERVOUS BECAUSE YOU'RE DEALING
WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT HAVE
SEVERAL FINAL THREE ALLIANCES.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU ANY
DIFFERENT?
>> OF COURSE NOT.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, WHAT WAS THE
SPECULATION ABOUT WHAT WAS
LABELED INFORMATION IN THE GAME?
>> I MEAN, I GUESS-- WHATEVER.
I-- I HAVE THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
I THINK EVERYONE KNEW THAT.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, THAT'S A BIG
DEAL TO HAVE AN IDOL ON DAY 33
WITH SEVEN PEOPLE LEFT.
>> YEAH, IT IS A BIG DEAL.
THAT'S A BIG DEAL.
IT'S JUST AS POWERFUL, PRETTY
MUCH, AS HAVING WHAT ERIK HAS
AROUND HIS NECK RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN USUALLY ONLY PLAY IT UP
UNTIL THE FINAL FIVE SO THERE
ARE LIMITED OPPORTUNITIES FOR
ANDREA TO PLAY IT IF SHE CHOOSES
TO DO SO.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, IS THAT THE
BIG QUESTION?
IT'S A HUGE ADVANTAGE IF YOU
USE WISELY.
>> EXACTLY.
IF I EVER FEEL THAT I'M PARANOID
OR ANYBODY, I COULD JUST PLAY
IT.
AND I KNOW MY PARANOIA IS PRETTY
HIGH, SO I COULD PLAY IT AT ANY
TIME, AND THEY COULD BE GOING
HOME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO, YOU
CANNOT VOTE FOR ERIK.
ANDREA HAS AN IDOL SHE MAY OR
MAY NOT PLAY.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS FAIR GAME.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
SHERRI, YOU'RE UP.
>> I THINK IT WAS THE MOMENT
THAT WE WERE BALANCING ON A
DOGHOUSE IN THE OCEAN FOR FOUR
HOURS THEY REALIZED YOU ARE A
HUGE THREAT AND NEED TO GO.
>> NEWER A SNEAKY, SNEAKY LITTLE
GIRL, ALWAYS READY TO BLINDSIDE
SOMEONE, BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE READY FOR THIS ONE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO
DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTE.
FIRST VOTE, BRENDA.
ANDREA.
EDDIE.
ONE VOTE BRENDA, ONE VOTE
ANDREA, ONE VOTE EDDIE.
EDDIE.
TWO VOTES EDDIE.
ANDREA.
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: BRENDA.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES BREND ATWO VOTES
EDDIE, TWO VOTES ANDREA, ONE
VOTE LEFT.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT, AND
THE FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ANDREA.
>> OH, YOU GUYS!
THAT WAS GOOD.
THAT WAS REALLY GOOD.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT A BIG MOVE FOR
WEEKS.
TONIGHT YOU MADE ONE.
THE QUESTION IS, NOW WHAT?
TBRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"."
>> I THINK IT SHOULD BE COCHRAN.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN'S IN TROUBLE.
>> DO I HAVE AN EXPIRATION DATE
THAT'S RAPIDLY APPROACHING.
>> Jeff: ERIK IS WITHERING
AWAY?
>> I'M TRYING TO DEFEAT MYSELF
AT THIS POINT.
I'VE GOT TO GET SOMETHING TO
EAT.
I WANT FOOD!
>> Jeff: AND A SURPRISE VISIT
FROM HOME CHANGING EVERYTHING.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> UNFORTUNATELY, I WAS
CONFIDENT WITH THIS PLAN THAT I
SET UP THAT I WASN'T EVEN
THINKING ABOUT PLAYING THE IDOL.
I SHOULD HAVE LEARNED MY LESSON
THE FIRST TIME.
WHEN THE DAY'S REALLY CALM AND
YOU'RE NAPPING AND FEEL
COMFORTABLE, YOU'RE PROBABLY
GOING TO GET BLINDSIDES AND IT
WILL PROBABLY HAPPEN AGAIN.
BUT I WILL ALWAYS HAVE THIS
BEAUTIFUL NECKLACE SOUVENIR THAT
WILL REMIND ME ABOUT TRUSTING
PEOPLE TOO MUCH.