>> Jeff: THIS IS THE CARAMOAN
ISLANDS.
A STUNNING PARADISE, AND A
DANGEROUS WILDERNESS.
THESE 10 AMERICANS ARE ABOUT TO
BEGIN THE ADVENTURE OF A
LIFETIME.
>> IT IS DEFINITELY A SURREAL
EXPERIENCE THAT I'M HERE, AND I
AM GOING TO BE PLAYING THE GAME.
>> Jeff: THEY COME FROM
DIFFERENT WALKS OF LIFE.
>> I'VE BEEN ON OVER 60 COMBAT
MISSIONS IN IRAQ SO AS FAR AS
THIS GAME GOES, THEY'RE LUNCH
MEAT.
>> Jeff: BUT THEY HAVE ONE
THING IN COMMON-- THEY ARE ALL
FANS OF "SURVIVOR."
>> KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT THE GAME
AND I KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT PEOPLE
THAT I THINK I'LL MAKE IT TO THE
VERIEN.
>> Jeff: AND FIRST IMPRESSIONS
ARE ALREADY FORMING.
>> THERE IS ONE GUY WITH GLASS
WHO SEEMS PARTICULARLY OBSERVANT
OF EVERYBODY ELSE.
HE IS GOING TO BE ANOTHER
STRATEGIST, BESIDES MYSELF.
>> ONE OF THE BLONDE, GOOD LORD,
YOU COULD BREAK HER IN TWO, I
THINK, AND SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE'S,
LIKE, 18 YEARS OLD.
I'M LIKE, "WHAT IN THE HELL IS
SHE DOING OUT HERE?"
>> Jeff: BUT FLYING OVERHEAD,
THEIR COMPETITION.
10 FAVORITE SURVIVORS FROM PAST
SEASONS.
MALCOLM.
ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR TO EVER
PLAY CAME WITHIN ONE CHALLENGE
OF WINNING IT ALL.
BUT HE DROPPED THE BALL.
COCHRAN, THE SURVIVOR NERD.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC."
HE BETRAYED HIS TRIBE.
>> YOU THREW THE WHOLE TRIBE
UNDER THE BUS.
YOU DISUVMENT ME.
>> Jeff: HE PAID THE ULTIMATE
PRICE AND HE TOOK DAWN DOWN WITH
HIM.
HE TOLD HER HIS PLAN TO FLIP BUT
SHE WAS TOO LOYAL TO GO ALONG.
BRENDA, SHE USED HER LOOKS TO
HER ADVANTAGE.
>> SHIEZ A CUTE GIRL.
>> SHE'S GOING TO TAKE YOU GUYS
OUT ONE BY ONE.
>> Jeff: BUT NOT EVERYONE ON
HER TRIBE-- THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN-- WAS CHARMED.
>> IF WE WERE TO GIVE HIM THE
NECKLACE, THAT WOULD REDEEM HIM
AND HE WOULD VOTE FOR AMANDA.
>> WHO WOULD VOTE FOR THAT.
>> I WANT TO GIVE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY TO NATALIE.
>> THIS WILL GO DOWN AS THE
DUMBEST IN SURVIVOR EVER IS
THERE ERIK WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
TO GIVE UP IMMUNITY.
BRANDON WAS WILLING TO SACRIFICE
EVERYTHING TO PLAY THE HONEST
GAME HIS UNCLE, RUSSELL HANTZ,
NEVER COULD.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO SCREW ME
OR THERE ARE GOING TO BE
CONSEQUENCES.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, THE
HARDWORKING FARM GIRL.
>> MAYBE COME HANG OUT IN
WISCONSIN.
>> REALLY?
>> Jeff: SHE FLIRTED HER WAY
RIGHT OUT OF THE GAME.
ANDREA, THE TRIKE HAS SPOKEN.
CORINNE.
>> SHE WAS GOOD AT MAKING
FRIENDS.
BUT EVEN BETTER AT MAKING
ENEMIES.
>> SHOE ARE AN UNUNEMPLOYED,
UNEDUCATED, LEACH ON SOCIETY.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP.
>> HEY!
>> Jeff: HE WAS LABELED CRAZY
BY HIS TRIBE MATES.
>> SUDDENLY A GUY WHO WAS ABLE
TO BECOME A FEDERAL AGENT--
>> WHATEVER?
>>.
>> SUDDENLY BECOMES ( BLEEP )
CRAZY WITH SOME WHITE FOLKS THEY
LIKE TO TAKE A BLACK MAN AND
MAKE THEM CRAZY WHEN HE MAKES AN
ARGUMENT YOU TONIGHT WANT TO
HEAR.
>> Jeff: BUT HE ALIGNED WITH
ONE OF "SURVIVOR'S" BEST AND
MADE TO THE FINAL THREE.
NOW HE'LL HAVE TO CONTEND WITH A
FORMER RIFLE, FRANCESCA.
>> YOU ARE A CRAZY PERSON.
>> I AM SANE.
>> Jeff: BUT PHILLIP CAME OUT
THE VICTOR WHEN FRANCESCA WAS
VOTED OUT FIRST.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION ISLAND."
>> THE NAME OF THE GAME IS
PEOPLE WHO MAKE THE MISTAKES.
>> Jeff: WHAT WILL HAPPEN WHEN
THESE EXPLOSIVE PERSONALITIES
COLLIDE.
10 FAVORITES MUCH WORK TOGETHER
WHILE BATTLING THE ELEMENTS AND
THEIR EGOS.
10 FANS MUST LEARN THE GAME FAST
OR THEY'LL BE VOTED OUT.
IN THE END, ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
TO CLAIM THE MILLION-DOLLAR
PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> CAREFUL.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN!
WELCOME TO THE CARAMOAN ISLANDS.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
YOU GUYS READY TO SEE WHO YOU'RE
PLAYING AGAINST?
>> ABSOLUTELY!
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THIS SEASON YOU WILL
BE PLAYING AGAINST SOME OF YOUR
FAVORITE SURVIVORS FROM PAST
SEASONS.
BRING THEM IN!
FROM "SURVIVOR: SOUTH
PACIFIC,"
COCHRAN.
>> NERD ALERT!
>> Jeff: ALSO FROM "SURVIVOR:
SOUTH PACIFIC," DAWN.
>> DAWN!
OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: FROM "SURVIVOR:
GABON," CORINNE.
FROM "SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION
ISLAND" A ANDREA.
HE WAS A FAN THE FIRST TIME HE
PLAYED THIS GAME.
HE'S RETURNING AS A FAVORITE.
ERIK FROM "FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES."
FROM "SURVIVOR: PHILIPPINES,"
MALCOLM.
FROM "SURVIVOR: NICARAGUA,"
BRENDA.
>> SHE'S SO DANGEROUS.
>> Jeff: FROM "SURVIVOR: SOUTH
PACIFIC," BRANDON.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S RUSSELL'S NEPHEW!
>> Jeff: FROM "SURVIVOR:
REDEMPTION ISLAND," FRANCESCA.
AND ROUNDING OUT THE FAVORITE
TRIBE FROM "SURVIVOR: REDEMPTION
ISLAND," FORMER FEDERAL AGENT,
PHILLIP SHEPPARD.
>> Jeff: LET ME TELL YOU WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING.
IT IS "SURVIVOR: CARAMOAN - FANS
VS. FAVORITES" 2.
( APPLAUSE )
ARLET ME HAND YOU YOUR BUFFS.
FANS, PUT THEM ON.
FAVORITES, PUT THEM ON P.
>> GO, BIG ORANGE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE
START THINGS OFF WITH A LITTLE
CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> WRING IT!
>> WE NEED A LITTLE FIGHT!
>> WHOA!
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING
TO WORK, TWO MEMBERS FROM EACH
TRIBE ARE GOING TO RACE TO
RETRIEVE A RING.
YOU WILL THEN WORK TOGETHER TO
GET BACK TO YOUR FLAG POLE WITH
THE RING WHILE THE OTHER TRIBE
TRIES TO STOP YOU ANY WAY THEY
CAN.
THE FIRST TRIBEMEMBER TO HAVE
ONE HAND ON THEIR FLAG POLE, ONE
HAND ON THEIR RING, SCORES A
POINT FOR THEIR TRIBE.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
IF?
>> YES.
>> Jeff:YOU ARE PLAYING FOR AN
ELDERLY HEAD START IN THIS GAME
IN THE FORM OF FIRE.
( APPLAUSE )
NOBODY KNOWS BETTER THAN THE
GROUP OF FAVORITES HOW IMPORTANT
FIRE IS IN THIS GAME.
TO GO ALONG WITH THE
PHILANTHROPIST, 20 POUNDS OF
BEANS.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: WHICH THE OTHER TRIBE
WILL NOT HAVE.
THIS CHALLENGE TAKES PLACE IN
THE WATER.
FIGURE OUT WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO
WEAR.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> I WANT TO HIT SOMEBODY REALLY
HARD.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
FIRST ROUND, ONE MAN, ONE WOMAN
FROM THE FAVORITES.
FIRST ROUND GOING TO BE ERIK AND
DAWN TAKING ON ONE MAN, ONE
WOMAN.
JULIA AND SHAMAR.
YOU'LL START WITH A HAND ON THE
POLE.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST CHALLENGE, OF FAN VERIZON
FAVORITES 2.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ERIK OFF TO A FAST START.
HE'S GOING TO GET THAT RING
FIRST.
NOW HE'S GOT TO GET BACK.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: HE'S GOT A BIG BOY
COMING AFTER HIM.
ERIK GOING TO LAUNCH THAT.
IT'S UP FOR GRABS.
JULIA HAS IT!
DAWN TAKES DOWN JULIA.
THAT RING'S UP FOR DWRABZ.
SHAMAR NOW ON IT.
THIS COULD BE TOUGH TO BEAT
FANS SCORE THE FIRST POINT!
FANS LEAD ONE-ZIP.
WHO YOU PUTTING UP?
HOPE AND ANNIE TAKING ON BRANDON
AND ANDREA.
WHO WANTS IT MORE?
EDDIE NOW GOING TO TAKE OFF
AFTER THAT RING.
>> KEEP IT, KEEP IT!
>> Jeff:OON DEGREE AND HOPE
GOING AT IT.
ANDREA NOW PULLING HOPE.
>> GO GET IT, BRANDON!
>> Jeff: BRANDON IN ON IT.
EVERYBODY HAS A HAND ON THE RING
NOW.
EDDIE GETTING CLOSER AND CLOSER
TO THAT FAN FLAG POLE.
BRANDON NOW DRAGGING HIM OVER TO
THE FAVORITES' POLE.
HUGE EFFORT FOR BRANDON AND
ANDREA.
ANDREA VERY CLOSE.
CAN SHE REACH THE POLE?
YES!
FAVORITES SCORE.
WE ARE 1-1.
>> FAVORITES, BABY!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WAY TO GO!
>> Jeff: NEXT ROUND, SHERRI
AND MICHAEL FOR THE FANS, TAKING
ON PHILLIP AND BRENDA FOR THE
FAVORITES.
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
PLAYING TO 4.
SURVIVES READY?
GO!
MICHAEL HIGH-STEPPING IT TOWARD
THAT RING.
MICHAEL'S GOT THE RING FOR THE
FANS.
PHILLIP WANTING ON HIM.
PHILLIP GOING TO TAKE IT ON.
MICHAEL GOING HOD WITH PHILLIP.
HE'S NOT TOSSING THAT RING.
HE'S JUST HANGING ON
>> I'M A BIG BOY.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP NOW TRYING TO
GET IT AWAY FROM MICHAEL.
SHERRI AND BRENDA TIED UP.
>> BREAK HER WRIST!
>> Jeff: WHAT.
>> BREAK HER WRIST LIKE BREAK
HER HOLD.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY NOW IN ON
IT.
PHILLIP NOW WITH A STRATEGY THAT
WILL BE HARD TO STOP.
PHILLIP SCORES.
FAVORITES LEAD 2-1.
NEXT ROUND, MATT AND LAURA FOR
THE NANS.
UP AGAINST COCHRAN AND FRANCESCA
FOR THE FAVORITES.
FAVORITES LEAD 2-1.
HERE WE GO, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> Jeff: NOT RUNNING AT ALL.
NOBODY RUNNING IN THIS ROUND.
>> CORCORAN, YOU TAKE HER.
>> CORCORAN, YOU STAY WITH HER.
>> CORCORAN, YOU'RE ASKING TO
HAVE TO TAKE HER DOWN.
>> THINK YOU CAN HANDLE ME?
>> YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE WHAT I
CAN HANDLE.
>> Jeff: THE FAVORITES ARE
GOING TO LET MATT JUST HAVE IT.
FRANCESCA NOW GETTING INTO IT,
TRYING TO PULL THAT RING AWAY
FROM MATT.
CORCORAN NOW GET WET.
NOW WHO IS IN CONTROL IS THE
QUESTION?
EVERYBODY HAS A HAND ON THAT
RING.
CORCORAN TRIES TO TAKE DOWN
LARA.
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE, DON'T GIVE
UP!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES VERY CLOSE
TO THEIR FLAG POLE.
GOT TO HAVE ONE HAND ON THE
RING.
AND THEY DO!
FAVORITES SCORE!
FAVORITES LEAD 3-1!
>> THAT WAS AWESOME!
WAY TO GO FRAN AND COCHRAN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NEXT TWO.
CORINNE AND MALCOLM FROM THE
FAVORITES TAKING ON REYNOLD AND
ALLIE FROM THE FANS.
FAVORITES LEAD 3-1.
PLAYING TO 4.
>> THIS IS IT!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES COULD WIN
IT RIGHT HERE.
FANS NEED TO SCORE TO STAY
ALIVE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> YOU GOT IT!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM AND REYNOLD
BOTH SPRINTING IF THAT ARE RING.
REYNOLD'S GOING TO GET IT.
MALCOLM TAKES HIM DOWN.
ALLIE AND CORINNE NOW ON IT.
CORINNE TRYING TO TAKE ALLIE OUT
OF IT THIS.
REYNOLD LITERALLY PULLING
MALCOLM.
TWO OF THE BIGGEST GUYS OUT HERE
SQUARING OFF
MALCOLM LOSING HIS SHORTS.
>> GET THE RING!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY NOW WITH A
HAND BACK ON IT.
FAVORITES CAN WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
MALCOLM IS NOW THE ONE DRAGGING
EVERYBODY.
IT HAS BEEN A SHOWDOWN BETWEEN
MALCOLM AND REYNOLD, AND MALCOLM
IS FIGHTING BACK WITH HIS SHORTS
AROUND HIS KNEES.
>> COME ON!
MALCOLM!
CORINNE VERY CLOSE TO THAT POLE.
NOT QUITE.
CORINNE SLIPS OFF.
REYNOLD NOW FIGHTING BACK.
MALCOLM IS VERY CLOSE.
FAVORITES SCORE!
FAVORITES WIN THE FIRST
CHALLENGE!
>> YES!
YES!
>> NOT TOO MUCH, GUYS.
HEY, BRING IT IN.
BRING IT IN.
>> Jeff: FAVORITE, FLINT, WHO
WANTS IT?
GO GET IT, BRANDON.
>> Jeff: AND 20 POUND OF
BEANS!
>> I'LL TAKE THAT.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: FANS, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
BOAT'S WAITING TO TAKE YOU BACK
TO CAMP GET STARTED WORKING ON
YOUR SHELTER.
FAVORITES OFF TO A QUICK START.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP, GET STARTED
ON YOUR SHELTER.
>> TO ME THE CHALLENGE WITHOUT,
YOU KNOW, BEING THE WINNERS WAS
VERY DISAPPOINTING TO ME.
I HAD SO MUCH CONFIDENCE IN MY
TEAM, SO IT MADE ME, YOU KNOW,
REALIZE THAT, YOU KNOW, I DON'T
HAVE FULL CONTROL OVER THIS GAME
AND THEY JUST HAVE TO DO MY BEST
AND INSPIRE MY TEAMMATES, YOU
KNOW, TO DO A BETTER JOB NEXT
TIME.
>> WHERE IS OUR THEME MUSIC?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WHAT'S IN THERE?
>> RICE.
>> OH, THANK GOD!
>> WHEN WE SAW THE FLAG WE SAW
THE MACHETE AND THE BAG OF RICE
RIGHT THERE, WE ANY QUE IT WAS
REAL.
WE WERE HOME.
THIS BEAUTIFUL ISLAND WAS GOING
TO BE OUR HOME FOR THE NEXT 35
DAYS.
>> WE NEED WATER.
WE NEED TO START A FIRE.
SHELTER IS GREAT, BUT IF WE
DEHYDRATE, WE'LL DIE.
>> WE ALL HAD ONE CANISTER OF
WATER, AND IT WAS PRETTY MUCH
GONE AND WE REALIZED WE HAD TO
MAKE FIRE TO BE ABLE TO BOIL
WATER OR I MEAN WE WOULDN'T MAKE
IT TWO DAYS.
>> TO ME, SHELTER IS JUST AS
IMPORTANT AS FIRE.
AND THERE'S 10 PEOPLE ON OUR
TRIBE.
SO I'M JUST GOING TO DO MY THING
AND SEE HOW IT PLAYS OUT.
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN TWO PRETTIER
SUNBURNS.
>> THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS A
PRETTY SUNBURN.
>> YOU GUYS PUT A LOT OF ENERGY
INTO THAT ( BLEEP ) THAT WE
DON'T NEED RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> WE NEED FIRE, MAN.
>> THERE ARE CAN'T BE--
>> YOU GUYS HAVE ENERGY, PUT IT
TOWARD THE FIRE.
>> I'M NOT A FIRE MAKER.
I'M A SHELTER MAKER.
EVERYONE'S GOT THEIR JOB TO DO.
AND--
>> I WANT A DAMN SHELTER, I WANT
WATER, I WANT ALL OF IT BUT IF
SOMEONE DOESN'T WORK ON THE
SHELTER, THEN IT'S NOT GOING TO
GET DONE.
>> DO WHAT YOU WILL, MAN.
>> DIEWRKD I'M WORKING ON
SHELTER.
I'VE BEEN BUSTING MY ASS.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU LIFT ONE
SINGLE FINGER.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU LIFT A BAMBOO
OR CHOP ANYTHING.
I KIND OF HAD HIGHER
EXPECTATIONS FROM A MARINE.
>> MATT, YOU'RE DOING GREAT,
MAN.
>> I KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE I'M BUSTING MY ASS,
WHILE YOU'RE SITTING THERE.
>> WHO IS GETTING DOGGED?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, THOUGH?
WHAT ARE YOU REALLY DOING,
THOUGH?
WHAT HAVE YOU ACCOMPLISHED?
OH, I THINK YOU'RE GETTING ON
ME!
I THINK YOU'RE SAYING THIS!
AND I THINK YOU'RE SAYING THAT.
>> I'M A LITTLE BIT WORRIED
ABOUT HOW WE ARE GOING TO SIZE
UP AGAINST THE OTHER TRIBE NOW.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE COMING UP, AND WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE
CAMARADERIE IN CAMP OR ELSE
THINGS ARE GOING TO GET UGLY
QUICK.
>> DON'T NEED--
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> SHUT UP!
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU!
>> LANDING ON THIS BEACH, IT WAS
A LITTLE SURREAL, AND I'M
THINKING I'VE HAD THIS
EXPERIENCE.
I WAS WALKING ON A BEACH AND WE
WERE FINDING OUR CAMP.
DEFINITELY DIFFERENT AS FAR AS
THE ISLAND.
>> OH, SORRY.
>> I MEAN, THIS IS DINOSAURS OR
SOMETHING.
I MEAN, THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
>> THIS REALLY HAS A WAY OF
MAKING YOU FEEL UNATHLETIC.
>> YEAH.
>> I CAN'T EVEN WALK RIGHT NOW.
>> AS THE NEW KID ON THE BLOCK,
KIND OF, MY ROLE THE FIRST FEW
DAYS IS RAIL IMPRESSION
MANAGEMENT.
LUCKILY, I MANAGED TO WIN THE
GAME POINT AND WON US THE FLINT
AND THE BEANS, AND SO I GOT TO
MAKE A GREAT FIRST IMPRESSION ON
THE TRIBE, WHICH IS ACTUALLY
GREAT FOR MY STRATEGIC GAME.
>> THE FIRST TIME YOU COME OUT,
YOU'RE SO UNSURE.
THERE'S SO MUCH UNKNOWN.
YOU'RE WONDERING CAN I SURVIVE
THE HUMIDITY.
I CAN SURVIVE THE HEAT?
I CAN SURVIVE STARVATION?
CAN I DO IT?
I ALREADY KNOW I CAN DO IT.
THIS TIME WHEN I HIT THE BEACH I
WAS PROBABLY LIKE MY FATHER WHEN
HE WENT TO IWO JIMA IN WORLD WAR
II.
THEY WERE READY TO DEAL WITH
WHATEVER THEY HAD TO DEAL WITH.
IT WAS AWESOME FOR ME WHEN I
FIRST HIT THAT BEACH KNOWING I'M
READY, BABY.
>> PHILLIP, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> WHAT PLAN?
>> LIKE THE SHELTER PLAN?
>> MY PREFERENCE IS THIS IS
VERY, VERY TEMPORARY.
FOR ME I WANT TO BE FACING THE
OCEAN WHEN I WAKE UP IN THE
MORNING UPON I WANT TO LOOK AT
THE OCEAN.
>> YOU CAN JUST TURN YOUR HEAD.
>> NO.
>> YOU CAN GO LIKE THIS AND THEN
LIKE THAT.
>> TRUE.
>> LOOKING AT PHILLIP NOW, IT'S
HARD TO READ HIM.
I MEAN, I PRETTY MUCH STAND BY
MY INITIAL ASSESSMENT OF HIM AS
A CRAZY PERSON.
UM, BUT I'M HOPING THE FACT THAT
I WAS THE FIRST PERSON OUT MY
FIRST SEASON IS GOING TO WORK TO
MY ADVANTAGE BECAUSE THEY'RE
MUCH BIGGER THREAT IN THE GAME,
SO WHEN THEY'RE LOOK AROUND AND
WONDERING, YOU KNOW, WHO DO THEY
NEED TO BE WORRIED ABOUT,
HOPEFULLY THEY WON'T BE THINKING
ABOUT ME.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING?
>> IN TERMS OF?
>> BIG PICTURE-SMALL PICTURE.
>> WE HAVE TO STICK TOGETHER?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE LOYAL.
>> NO QUESTION.
>> TO A FAULT.
>> I RAIL WANT TO WORK WITH YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> SO I THINK, OKAY, US THREE
FOR SURE.
AND THEN I KNOW THAT COCHRAN IS
SO LOYAL.
>> COCHRAN WOULD STAY LOYAL TO
US.
>> HE WOULD, MAYBE US THREE--
ARE YOU SIT ON GETTING PHILLIP
OUT RIGHT AWAY?
>> I GUESS I WAS A LITTLE
TRAUMATIZED BY HAVING A REAL BAD
MINORITY LINE WHEN I FIRST
PLAYED AND NOW I'M LIKE I'M
GOING TO ALIGN WITH EVERYBODY.
>> US THREE, COCHRAN, BRANDON,
PHILLIP, THERE'S SIX.
>> OH, GOD!
>> LIKE PROBABLY--
>> LET'S NOT GET AHEAD OF OURS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK A LOT OF
PEOPLE THINK THAT MY FIRST
SEASON I GOT KIND OF A RAW DEAL
AND GOT STUCK IN AN IMPOSSIBLE
SITUATION, WHICH I TOTALLY
AGREE.
AND SO I'VE GOT TO PROVE THAT
THAT'S THE CASE AND THAT I
ACTUALLY CAN PLAY THIS GAME AND,
YOU KNOW, BE SMART ABOUT IT AND
BE COMPETITIVE AND MAKE THE
RIGHT RELATIONSHIPS AND GET
ALONG WITH PEOPLE AND BE A
SERIOUS THREAT IN THIS GAME.
I GUESS I WANT TO START OUT BY
SAYING THAT, YOU KNOW, EVEN
THOUGH WE DIDN'T GET ALONG SO
WELL.
>> UH-HUH.
>> THE FIRST TIME WE PLAYED
TOGETHER, YOU KNOW, I WAS NEVER
GUNNING FOR YOU.
AND I KNOW THAT YOU THOUGHT THAT
I WAS, BUT I HOPE YOU KNOW NOW
THAT WHEN I TOLD YOU THAT I
WASN'T, I WAS TELL YOU THE
TRUTH.
>> I'M GOING TO LET FRANCESCA BE
FRANCESCA.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS I
BURIED THE HATCHET WITH HER WHEN
SHE CAME UP TO ME HERE AND HAD A
CONVERSATION WITH ME, I REALIZE
SHE'S STUCK IN A TIME WARP.
I JUST THINK THAT-- SHE ANNOYS
ME GREATLY.
WE'RE PLAYING A NEW GAME.
>> YEAH.
>> BE SMART ABOUT IT.
>> NO, THAT'S ALL-- THAT'S WHAT
I'M TRYING TO DO.
>> TODAY, WE'RE ON THE SAME
TEAM.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY?
>> THAT'S HOW I FEEL,
ABSOLUTELY.
>> WE'VE GOT A JOB TO DO.
>> FILL.
AND I I HAD OUR FIRST
CONVERSATION.
IT WAS FINE.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I RESIGNED
MYSELF TO JUST PLAYING REALLY
NICE WITH PHILLIP.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S
GOING TO BE GUNNING FOR ME.
I'M NOT GUNNING FOR HIM.
SO IF I AM VOTED OFF FIRST A
SECOND TIME, I WILL EAT-- THIS
ROCK.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> GETTING VOTED OUT IS ONE
THING, BUT I'M NOT GOING TO SIT
UP HERE AND BE THE GUY WHO GOES
OUT FOR DEHYDRATION.
THAT'S NOT, YOU KNOW, SOMETHING
THEY COULD HAVE LIVED WITH, SO I
JUST STARTED LOOKING AT PEOPLE
MAKE THE FIRE AND I STARTED
SEEING WHERE THEY WERE GOING
WRONG.
>> DIDT GOT WARM BUT IT BARELY
BURNED.
>> I SAT BACK ON THE LOG AND I
WAS LIKE ALL RIGHT SO I NEED
THIS KIND OF WOOD.
I NEED TO DO THIS.
I NEED TO DO THAT.
>> THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
>> THIS HOLE IS TOO BIG FOR ME,
MAN.
WE'LL USE THIS WOOD RIGHT HERE,
CUT A LITTLE RIVET IN IT.
I'M GOING TO BE THE MARINE WHO
CAME IN AT THE END AND SMASHED
THEM.
ONCE IT STARTS SMOKING, LIGHT
BLOWS, AND WE CAN MAKE IT
HAPPEN.
WE, FOR REAL.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> WE CAN MAKE THIS HAPPEN.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> YOU'RE COMFORTABLE, RIGHT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> HELLO?
>> I SEE AN EMBER.
I SEE AN EMBER.
KEEP GOING.
FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
EMBER.
>> HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
>> HELP!
>> KEEP IT EASY.
THE OTHER SIDE.
>> KEEP IT GOING.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH!
>> GET SOME WOOD.
>> OKAY, GUYS, GET SOME MORE,
GET SOME MORE.
>> KEEP BLOWING IT, KEEP BLOWING
IT.
>> IF WE GOT DEHYDRATED JUST OFF
THE FIRE, I KNEW WE HAD WATER
AROUND THE CORNER.
I HAD TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
IT WAS LIKE BEING IN IRAQ AND
HAVING TO GET HOME.
IT JUST HAD TO HAPPEN.
>> YEAH!
>> LOOK AT MY FACE.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
>> SIGNS SAW EVERYONE OVER BY
THE FIRE, I KNEW THAT IT WAS
GREAT NEWS.
OBVIOUSLY, WE NEED FIRE.
I WAS EXTREMELY HAPPY.
>> I LOAF YOU, MAN.
I LOVE YOU.
>> I SMOOTH IT OVER WITH SHAMAR.
WE SHOOK HAND.
SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA GIVE A GUY
THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT, A
LITTLE BIT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> OH, MY GOD.
I NEED A SECOND SCOOP, AFTER
EVERYBODY HAS HAD SOME.
IT'S CRISPY HEAVEN!
>> WE'RE HAPPY SEE YOU HAPPY.
>> WE HAVE SUCH A GOOD CROWD.
WHEN I LOOK AT EVERYBODY IN
THERE, I'M THINKING THIS IS
GOING TO BE A GOOD GAME.
I THOUGHT SOME THINGS I LEARNED
FROM BOSTON ROB MIGHT COME TO
THEY PLAYWORKING WITH THIS
GROUP.
I CREATED SOMETHING CALLED "THE
B.R. RULES."
B.R. RULE ONE WOULD BE BE IN AN
ALLIANCE.
RULE TWO, BE AN ALLIANCE WITHIN
A ALLIANCE.
RULE THREE, GET RID OF YOUR
ALLIANCE BEFORE THEY GET RID OF
YOU.
AND YOU DON'T OWE ANYBODY
ANYTHING.
IT'S ALL ABOUT FAMILY.
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
>> TELL ME.
>> WHAT I WOULD LIKE TO TRY TO
DO WITH YOU, GET IN AN ALLIANCE
EARLY AND I WOULD LIKE TO GET
MALCOLM AND ANDREA.
>> I'M IN.
I LOVE IT.
>> I'M PLAYING A DIFFERENT
STRATEGY THIS TIME.
FIRST OF ALL, FIND TWO PEOPLE
THAT ARE VERY EFFICIENT AT
DOMINATING THE TRIBE, MAKING
SURE WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
I PICK CORINNE.
I GAVE EVERYONE A NAME, YOU'RE
DOMINATRIX.
CORINNE IS A TAKE CHARGE TYPE OF
PERSON.
AND ANDREA, BECAUSE I KNEW HER.
I KNEW HER TO BE A STRATEGIST.
>> IF WE WANTED TO GO, LIKE, US,
AND FILM, THE STRONGER PEOPLE SO
WE DON'T TOTALLY SUCK.
>> I'M FOR IT.
>> PART OF MY STRATEGY WAS TO
HAVE TWO PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
MALCOLM IS IN.
I WANT DAWN.
I WOULD BE IN THE BACKGROUND.
BECAUSE I AM BEING STEALTH, THE
UNDERCOVER BROTHER, FOR SURE,
THE SPECIALIST, BEHIND THE
SCENES, GIVING DIRECTION,
WITHOUT MAKING IT SO
EVERYBODY, EXCEPT MY CORE
ALLIANCE.
I LOOK AT YOU, AND YOU OF I SEE
HOW YOU PLAY THE GAME.
HENCE, YOU'RE THE INTELLIGENTIA
ATTACHE.
I HAVE GONE OUT AND RECRUITED
SIX PEOPLE.
>> HAVING FUN?
>> GOOD.
I'M HAVING FUN, TOO.
BUT I'M LOOK AT ERIK.
THERE'S SOMETHING THERE THAT I
LIKE.
RIGHT NOW I THINK I HAVE THE
NUMBERS WHERE IF I DIDN'T BRING
YOU IN, LET'S SAY, FOR EXAMPLE,
PEOPLE I'M ALIGNED WITH COULD
STILL CONTROL THINGS HERE.
>> GOTCHA.
>> BUT I WANT YOU IN.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T GET
NERVOUS.
>> SOMETIMES I DO GET A LITTLE
NERVOUS, BUT--
>> IT'S GOING TO REQUIRE YOU TO
COMPLETELY TRUST ME 100%.
>> GO AHEAD, GO AHEAD.
SORRY, SORRY.
YOU'RE GOING TO TRUST SOMEBODY
OUT HERE, ANYWAY.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW HOW IT GOES.
FAIR ENOUGH.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BRING
SOMEBODY TO THE PARTY THAT DON'T
WANT TO COME.
AND BY THE WAY, I'M JUST THE
MESSENGER.
I WAS SENT.
I'M AN ERRAND BOY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SO DON'T THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO RUN BACK THERE AND SAY,
"GUESS WHAT?"
YOU HAVE THE WRONG PERSON.
>> PHILLIP BASICALLY SAID TO ME,
"YOU'RE WITH ME OR YOU'RE OUT."
IT'S NOT EVEN A CHOICE, WHICH
DRIVES ME NUTS.
THE FACT THAT HE CAME TO ME WITH
THIS FEAR MENTALITY WITH A
BOSTON ROB STYLE, I DON'T WANT
TO BE WITH HIM.
HE'S A COMBATIVE IDIOT LOSER WHO
MAKES EVERYBODY CRAZY.
>> PRETTY CLEAR WE HAVE TO STICK
TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
YOU AND I.
>> YEAH.
>> ARE A HUNTED SPECIES OUT
HERE.
>> I KNOW.
WE'RE DEFINITELY TARGETS ON OUR
BACK.
>> WE'D BE STUPID NOT TO.
>> YEAH.
>> SO THAT WAS COOL WE GOT
PAIRED UP IN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
TODAY.
>> YEAH, THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> I DEFINITELY WANT TO BE WITH
YOU.
>> ME, TOO.
>> I MEAN, I THINK IF WE JUST
WATCH OUT FOR EACH OTHER, NO
MATTER WHAT, CRAZY ALLIANCES ARE
GOING TO HAPPEN AND GET BROKEN.
LIKE, I'M TALKING ABOUT ALL THE
WAY TO THE LAST TWO.
>> ME AND YOU TO THE LAST TWO.
SWEAR TO GOD?
>> SWEAR TO GOD.
I THINK IT WAS SERENDIPITOUS
THAT I GOT PAIRED UP WITH ALY IN
THE CHALLENGE.
WE SHOULD ACT LIKE WE ARE
GETTING ROCKS WHICH WE ARE.
I KNEW THE GUYS WOULD WANT TO
PAIR UP WITH ME AND THERE'S NO
PRESSURE TO THAT.
BUT WHAT I NEEDED INSTANTLY WAS
SOMEBODY WHO WAS NOT OBVIOUS.
AND I THINK SHE'S AN OBVIOUS
CHOICE.
SHE KIND OF FLIES UNDER THE
RADAR.
SHE'S NOT THE CUTEST.
SHE'S NOT THE ANYTHING.
SHE'S JUST COOL AND LIKABLE.
#-R I'M NOT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO SCREW ME
OVER, ARE YOU?
>> PROMISE.
>> "SURVIVOR" IS A GAME OF GUT
INSTINCT, AND RIGHT NOW MY GUT
FEELS GOOD.
AND I THINK HERS DOES, TOO.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW MANY
STARS ARE OUT.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S WILD.
>> YOU CAN SEE SO MANY MORE OUT
HERE.
>> IT'S LIKE MY BEDROOM WHEN I
WAS A CHILD.
>> MINE ARE STILL UP, I THINK.
>> I'LL FEELING NOSTALGIC.
SO WE'RE STICKING TOGETHER.
>> UM.
>> I'M ONLY ASKING BECAUSE I
LIKE TO THINK THIS WE HAVE,
LIKE, A CONNECTION.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE WE'RE THE ONLY
TWO WHO--
>> ME AND HOPE ARE THE TWO
BESTED LOOKING PEOPLE HERE, I
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I'M NOT JUST SAYING THAT.
THAT'S HOW IT IS.
AS SOON AS WE GOT OFF THE BOAT
WE WERE PARTNERS WITH THE
CHALLENGE.
AND I'M LIKE I'M GOING TO WORK
WITH YOU.
AND SHE'S LIKE I'M GOING TO WORK
SO WE'RE STICKING TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, THAT'S THE
PLAN.
ME, YOU... I DON'T KNOW.
WHO ELSE?
>> I LIKE REYNOLD.
HE'S MY BOY.
>> I DO, TOO.
>> I LIKE ALLIE.
>> YEAH.
>> HOPE, SHE'S LIKE A LITTLE
SOUTHERN BELLE.
THAT'S WHAT I LOOKING FOR-- I
DON'T KNOW IF I'M LOOKING TO
SLOW DANCE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE FUN.
YOU'RE MY SOUTHERN BELLE FOR THE
NEXT MONTH.
I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME.
>> THE FIRST NIGHT, EVERYBODY
WAS REALLY JUST LOOKING FOR BODY
WARMTH, SO IT WAS JUST LIKE WE
WERE ALL PILING IN.
BUT I DID NOTICE BECAUSE I WAS
SLEEPING NEXT TO REYNOLD AND
ALLIE, THAT THEIR CUDDLING WAS A
LITTLE BIT MORE.
I NOTICED A LITTLE BIT MORE ARMS
LOCKED AROUND.
YOU KNOW, IT WASN'T JUST A BODY
WARMTH THING.
NOT A SMART MOVE.
ROMANTIC ALLIANCES DO NOT WORK
ON "SURVIVOR."
YOU'RE GOING TO GET TARGETED
RIGHT AWAY.
>> IT'S HOT RIGHT NOW, RIGHT?
>> IT'S REALLY HOT.
>> I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE I
ONLY ASK BECAUSE I WANT TO MAKE
SURE I'M NOT FEEFERLISHLY--
>> NO IT'S HOT.
IT'S REALLY HOT.
>> WHETHER-WISE, THIS IS NOT MY
ENVIRONMENT.
I WAS NOT AWARE HOW QUICKLY I
CAN BECOME SUNBURNED.
THE SUN IS CONSTANTLY ROASTING
YOU.
MY ENTIRE BODY, HEAD TO TOE--
LITERALLY, MY TOES ARE
SUNBURNED.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> HOW IS THAT HAPPENING?
THEY'RE SO SWOLLEN.
>> LOOK AT HIS FEET.
THEY'RE SWOLLEN.
>> OH, MAN, THAT'S BAD.
>> THEY FEEL VERY, VERY TIGHT.
I GUESS THEY ARE SWOLLEN.
>> COCHRAN IS LIKE A LITTLE
TOMATO RIGHT NOW.
HE IS ALL BRIGHT RED ALL OVER
THE PLACE AND HE IS SWOLLEN LIKE
A LITTLE PREGNANT LADY.
>> I CAN'T MOVE.
I'M BURNING.
WHEN I MOVE I GET EXHAUSTED.
IF WE HAD A CHALLENGE RIGHT NOW,
I'D ACTUALLY DIE.
I'M TRYING TO PUT ON A BRAVE
FACE, MAYBE MAKE SOME
SELF-DEPRECATING COMMENTS AROUND
CAMP-- OH, YEAH, I LOOK LIKE A
LOBSTER, I LOOK LIKE A FREAK.
I'M IN PAIN RIGHT NOW.
I'M TRYING TO STAY STRONG.
MY NEW PERSONA IS STRONG, A
LITTLE SWAGGER.
I CAN'T BE THE SAME FREAK I WAS
LAST TIME.
>> OUTSIDE OF THIS ISLAND, I
WOULD HANG OUT WITH YOU GUYS.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH THE SAME.
>> IT FEELS MORE NATURAL.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF HOURS IN
THE DAY.
STRATEGY OR NO STRATEGY, YOU
HAVE TO HANG OUT.
ALLIE AND I I HAD A LITTLE
CUDDLE SESSION LAST NIGHT, AND A
LOT IS COMMUNICATED THROUGH THE
CUDDLE.
SO NOW WE KIND OF HAVE THIS FOUR
WITH ME, EDDIE, ALLIE, AND HOPE.
SO IT'S ALL KIND OF WORKED OUT.
>> WE'RE ALL GOING TOW TRY NOT
TO BE CLICHE AND HAVE THE COOL
KIDS HANG OUT, BUT IT HAPPENS.
>> HOLLY ALL OVER AGAIN.
>> OH!
>> THAT'S TRUE, THOUGH.
>> BUT IT IS TRUE.
>> THIS IS, LIKE THE COOL KID
LUNCH TABLE BACK AT HOLLY.
EVERYBODY WANTS TO SIT AT THE
COOL KID LUNCH TABLE.
YOU HAVE TO WORK YOUR WAY IN.
BUT I DON'T THINK ANYBODY ELSE
IS GOING TO BE AT OUR TABLE.
>> I'M NOT KIDDING.
>> DID YOU SAY SOMETHING ABOUT A
WEIRD VIBE THIS MORNING?
>> UH-HUH.
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK SLEEPING SITUATIONS
KIND OF SAID A LOT LAST NIGHT.
>> I AGREE.
>> THERE'S LOTS OF SNUGGLING
GOING ON LAST NIGHT.
IT WASN'T JUST A, "I'M STAYING
WARM," KIND OF CUDDLE, SNUGGLE
KIND OF THING.
THEY WERE HOOK UP.
WE HAVE TO BREAK UP THE COUPLE.
>> I DEFINITELY DON'T THINK I'LL
BE ABLE TO GET CLOSE WITH THOSE
FOUR.
>> OKAY, I'M WITH YOU.
>> GUYS, GUYSES, I'M 100%.
>> REAL QUICK, REAL QUICK.
>> OKAY.
>> I TOLD THE LADIES THAT I WAS
WITH HEM.
"OH, YEAH, I'M WITH YOU GUYS."
BUT I'M TRYING TO SET MYSELF UP
SO THAT I CAN BE HIP TO EITHER
DIRECTION BECAUSE I WANT TO GO
WHERE IT'S BEST FOR ME.
>> THIS THING ON MY LEC IS ALL
BALDNESS, LIKE A WIZARD ZORB.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MATT AND I, WE BOTH HAVE A
GREAT SENSE OF HUMOR, I THINK.
HE'S LAID BACK, AND HE WORKS
HARD SO WE KIND OF, YOU KNOW,
VIBE IN CAMP THE SAME WAY.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE
FREAKING OUT AND TALK.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, THERE'S A
LOT GOING ON.
THERE'S A CIRCLE OF LADIES THAT
CIRCLED AROUND ME WHILE YOU WERE
GONE.
I TOLD THEM I WAS IN WITH THEM
BUT I'M TOTALLY OPEN TO ANOTHER
OPTION IF YOU FEEL STRONGER
ABOUT SOMETHING.
>> MIKE CELL KIND OF, LIKE, TELL
ME, THERE ARE A COUPLE OF
DIFFERENT ALLIANCE POSSIBILITIES
THAT HAVE COME UP AND THEY'RE
REALLY STRONG OPTIONS, AND HE
WANTS TO KNOW WHERE I STAND.
>> YOU KNOW, THERE ARE PLUSES
AND MINUSES TO BOTH OPTIONS.
>> YEAH, IT'S ONE OF THOSE WEIRD
THINGS BECAUSE EVERYONE IS KIND
OF JUMPING THE GUN AND WE DON'T
WANT TO LOOK TOO YOU KNOW--
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> THREATENING OFF THE BAT.
>> I TOABLGTHSLY AGREE.
FOR ME, YOU AND I WE WILL DECIDE
TOGETHER WHICH WAY WAIT TO GO.
>> IF WE WIN IMMUNITY AND DON'T
HAVE TO GO TO TRIBEAND KEEP
WINNING, WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE
TO MAKE THAT DECISION FOR A
WHILE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> WOW!
>> COCHRAN, THAT IS THE WORST
SUNBURN I'VE EVER SEEN ON
SURVIVOR.
>> YOU'RE NOT SEEING THE HALF OF
IT.
IT'S PRETTY RIDICULOUS.
>> TRUE.
>> Jeff: WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> INSTANTLY.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO YOUR FIRST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT GOES.
ON MY GO, YOU WILL RACE OUT IN
PAIRS UP A FOUR-STORY TOWER.
AT EACH 44 YOU WILL FIND THREE
CRAITS FILLED WITH SANDBAGS.
YOU TOSS THEM OVER THE SIDE,
RACE BACK DOWN, THE NEXT PAIR
GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE TOSSED ALL 12 CRAITS
OVER, THE REMAINING PAIR WILL
RACE IN, GRAB THE SANDBAGS, AND
ATTEMPT TOW LAND THEM IN A
SERIES OF TARGETS.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET ONE SANDBAG
IN EACH OF THEIR SIX SPOTS WINS
IMMUNITY.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT RIGHT
HERE.
WITH IMMUNITY IN YOUR
POSSESSION, YOU CANNOT BE VOTED
OUT.
THAT IS THE KEY.
WITHOUT IT, YOU ARE VULNERABLE.
WINNING TRIBE, SAFE.
LOSING TRIBE GOODS TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE FIRST PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, FANS, IF YOU WIN,
YOU ARE ALSO STILL PLAYING FOR
FLINT.
BIG STAKES.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
COCHRAN IS UP FIRST FOR THE
HEROES, SHERRY AND LAURA UP
FIRST FOR THE FANS.
CANNOT TOSS THE CRATES UNTIL
BOTH TRIBE MEMBERS THERE.
GO!
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> GO!
>> Jeff: COCHRAN AND PHILLIP
HEADING DOWN.
LAUREN AND SHERRI HEADING DOWN.
>> COME BACK!
COME BACK!
>> Jeff: FRANCESCA AND CORINNE
NOW OUT FOR THE FAVORITES.
MICHAEL AND HOPE OUT FOR THE
FANS.
THIS PAIR HAS TO GO UP TWO
FLOORS.
WE DEAD EVEN RIGHT NOW.
GOTTA WAIT UNTIL BOTH ARE THERE.
START TOSSING.
>> GO!
GO!
>> GRAB THEM, GRAB THEM!
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> COME OMIKE!
>> Jeff: FANS NOW IN A BIT OF
A LEAD.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> COME ON, LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: THE ONLY WAY UP IS ON
THE LADDER.
THE ONLY WAY DOWN IS ON THE FIRE
POLE.
>> GOOD JOB!
GOOD JOB!
>> MADE UP SOME TIME!
>> THERE GO JULIA AND MATT FOR
THE FANS.
>> COME OCOME ON.
>> Jeff: ERR AND I CAN BRENDA
FOR THE FAVORITES.
ERIK FLYING UP THAT LADDER.
ERIK IS LEAPING TO THE TOP.
JULIA FLYING UP THIS LADDER.
>> GO, JULIA!
>> GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: GO!
>> WAY TO GO, MATT.
>> Jeff: MATT IS TOSSING.
ERIK'S TOSSING!
>> PERFECT.
>> NICE JOB, GUYS.
COME BACK, COME BACK!
>> Jeff: WE ARE STILL DEAD
EVEN THREE FLOORS IN.
BRENDA FLIES DOWN THAT POLE.
THIS IS NECK AND NECK.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: BRANDON AND ANDREA,
THE LAST PAIR FOR THE FAVORITE.
EDDY AND ALLIE, THE LAST PAY FOR
THE FANS.
NOW YOU'RE GOING FOUR FLOORS UP.
FOUR LADDERS UP.
FOUR POLLS COMING DOWN.
BRANDON GETS TO THE TOP FIRST.
GO, BRANDON!
EDDIE WAITING ON ALLIE.
HE CAN'T GO UNTIL SHE'S THERE.
>> OH, BABY!
>> DO IT!
DO IT!
>> Jeff: GO, FANS!
FAVORITES NOW TAKE THE LEAD, AND
THEY'RE FLYING DOWN!
>> ANDREA!
>> Jeff: FANS HAVE FALLEN
BEHIND.
>> YES!
YES!
TAKE IT!
>> Jeff: BRANDON AND ANDREA
SMOKING THIS COURSE!
MALCOLM AND DAWN WILL NOW BE
DOING THE COLLECTING OF SANDBAGS
AND AS ALLIE AND EDDIE RACE
BACK.
GOT SIX TARGETS YOU NEED TO HIT.
FANS, YOU NEED TO PICK IT UP!
>> HUSTLE!
HUSTLE!
COME BACK DOWN!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM TOSSING FOR
THE FAVORITES.
MALCOLM SCORES ONE FOR THE
FAVORITES.
IT IS REYNOLD AND SHAMAR
COLLECTING SANDBAGS FOR THE
FANS.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM SCORES
ANOTHER.
MALCOLM SCORES ANOTHER ONE FOR
THE FAVORITES.
THE FAVORITES WITH THREE.
REYNOLD AND SHAMAR HAVE
COLLECTED THEIR SANDBAGS.
REYNOLD IS GOING TO TOSS FOR THE
FANS.
COME ON, REYNOLD!
>> Jeff: JUST MISSING.
REYNOLD SCORES ONE FOR THE FANS.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, CLOSE BUT NO
GO.
REYNOLD SCORES ANOTHER ONE FOR
THE FANS.
THE FANS WITH TWO.
REYNOLD SCORES ANOTHER.
WE ARE 3-3.
IT IS 4-3, FANS.
5-3, FANS.
PHEIFFER-4, FANS.
5-4, FANS.
REYNOLD HAS ONE LEFT.
MALCOLM NEEDS TWO.
>> COME ON, BABY, COME ON!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM JUST MISSES
AGAIN.
THE FANS NEED ONE MORE BAG, AND
THERE IT IS!
FANS WIN FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE!
FANS, CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE )
NICE WAY TO START.
IMMUNITY AND FLINT.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FAVORITE, AFTER ONLY
THREE DAYS IN THIS GAME,
SOMEBODY FROM YOUR TRIBE WILL BE
THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"FANS VERSUS FAVORITE."
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
FANS, NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> IT WAS A HEARTBREAKER.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, YOU CAN BE
CONFIDENT, AND WE WERE
CONFIDENT, BUT THERE'S SUCH A
THING AS LUCK AND THAT GUY,
REYNOLD, HE WAS JUST REALLY GOOD
AT TOSSING SANDBAGS INTO HOLES,
APPARENTLY SOME SKILL THAT IF IT
HAD TAKEN HIM 10 SECONDS LONGER
WE WOULD HAVE WON.
UNFORTUNATELY WE'RE GOING TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
YEAH, SO, THAT SUCKS THAT WE
LOST.
>LOST, BUT I THINK PHILLIP.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, HAVE YOU GUYS TALKED
ABOUT THE GAME AT ALL?
>> CUTE NICKNAMES AND STUFF BUT
NOT ABOUT ACTUAL GAME PLAY.
HE'S LIKE YOU'RE A SMART MAN.
I RESPECT YOU.
>> IF WE DIDN'T DO PHILLIP I
LIKE CORINNE.
>> SEE, I LIKE CORINNE.
>> I LIKE HER TOO, IT'S NOT
THAT--
>> I BROUGHT YOU A WET BUFF.
>>OTS NOT THAT I DON'T LIKE HER,
I DO.
BUT IF CORINNE HAD COME TO ME
YESTERDAY AND SAID LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE GAME, WHAT ARE YOU
THINKING?
THAT WOULD MAKE ME TRUST HER
MORE BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE MORE
IN KEEPING WITH WHO I PERCEIVE
HER TO BE.
THE FACT THAT, "EVERYTHING'S
GREAT.
WE'RE PLAYING SURVIVOR?
WE VOTE PEOPLE OUT?
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT."
THAT MAKES ME SUSPICIOUS OF HER.
>> YOU NEED TO PUT THAT ON YOUR
HEAD.
JUST GO LIKE-- GO LIKE THIS.
>> SQUEEZE IT ON TO YOUR HEAD.
>> LIKE THIS.
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT IS
DELIGHTFUL!
I FEEL, LIKE, 10 YEARS YOUNGER.
>> YOU LOOK IT.
THERE IT IS.
>> SUNBURN ASIDE, I HAVE
BASICALLY INSTANT RAPPORT WITH--
I SAY EVERYBODY ON MY TRIBE IS
INTENSELY SATISFYING.
IT'S BASICALLY THE ALOE TO MY
SUNBURN, AS IT WERE.
>> HEY, BRANDON.
>> HOW ARE YOU GUYS?
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> HEY.
>> PHILLIP.
>> OKAY.
>> UNLESS YOU HAVE A DIFFERENT
IDEA WHO ELSE COULD IT POSSIBLY
BE?
>> GO WITH THE FLOW.
>> WHAT DOES EVERYONE ELSE
THINK?
WE HAVE ENOUGH, RIGHT?
>> WELL, THIS IS FIVE--
>> IS BRENDAN WITH YOU?
IS BRENDAN-- NO?
>> I DON'T THINK THERE'S GOING
TO BE ANYONE.
>> FRANCESCA IS TRICKY FOR ME
BECAUSE I REALLY LIKE HER.
SHE'S FUNNY.
I THINK WE HAVE A PRETTY GOOD
BOND.
IT'S JUST-- IT'S HARD BECAUSE WE
TALKED, LIKE, RIGHT AWAY.
HER, ME, AND DAWN, BUT THEN A
LONG TIME WENT BY AND I DIDN'T
HEAR ANYTHING FROM HER.
SO SHE HAS HER OWN AGENDA BUT I
THINK I HAVE MORE LOYAL PEOPLE
WITH PHILLIP, SO INSTEAD OF
FRANCESCA, IT'S ALMOST BETTER TO
GO THAT WAY.
>> I HEARD STRATEGY TALK.
AND I'M LIKE I SHOULD TALK TO
FRANCESCA SO SHE DOESN'T YOU
KNOW SO SHE THINKS A LOT OF US
ARE ON BOARD WITH HER.
AND I WAS LIKE SO, LIKE, WHAT'S
UP?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
AND SHE'S THINKING OF YOU.
LIKE, SHE NEEDS TO GO.
>> WHAT.
>> I THINK SHE NEEDS TO GO.
>> I TOLD YOU.
SHE'S ALWAYS STRATEGIZING.
SHE DOESN'T WAIT.
SHE'S NOT PATIENT.
SHE NEEDS TO GO.
I LIKE THE IDEA OF VOTING
FRANCESCA OUT FIRST AGAIN.
YOU NEED TO BE LIKE MACHIAVELLI
WHO SAID,, IF YOU COME AT ME
ONCE, I WILL BURN YOUR VILLAGE.
I WILL KILL YOUR AUNTS, UNCLES
AND ALL YOUR CHILDREN SO NONE OF
YOUR KIND WILL EXIST AGAIN
OPINION
>> OH!
>> SO I GUESS PHILLIP, HUH?
>> DEFINITELY.
HE SAID, "I'VE GOT A CHOICE FOR
YOU."
HE SAID, "YOU'RE EITHER WITH ME,
OR YOU'RE NOT BUT IF YOU'RE NOT
WE STILL HAVE THE NUMBERS
ANYWAY."
SO ME BASICALLY DIDN'T EVEN GET
ME A CHOICE.
HE SAID, "YOU'RE WITH ME OR
YOU'RE DEAD," BASICALLY.
HE SCARES ME PHILLIP BASICALLY
APPROACHED ME ON THE FIRST DAY
AND HE SAID, "YOU CAN BE WITH ME
AND WE HAVE THE NUMBERS OR CAN
BE AGAINST ME, AND I HAVE THE
NUMBERS ANYWAY."
MAYBE HE DOES HAVE THE NUMBERS.
MAYBE PHILLIP DOES HAVE ENOUGH
PEOPLE THAT HE CAN CONTROL THE
GAME, BUT I'M NOT SURE WHAT
PHILLIP'S UP TO.
HE'S QUIET.
HE'S JUST HANGING OUT.
HE'S NOT SCRAMBLING TOO MUCH.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S UP HIS
SLEEVE.
>> I'VE ALREADY SPOKEN WITH ERIK
JUST NOW.
>> OH, YEAH, OKAY.
HE'S TOTALLY FINE, RIGHT?
>> HE SAID THERE'S NO DOUBT IN
HIS MIND HE WANTS PHILLIP GONE
FIRST BUT HE SAID PHILLIP CAME
TO HIM AND SAID HE HAD NUMBERS,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
>> REALLY?
THEY HAVE NUMBERS.
HOW ARE CORINNE AND PHILLIP
NUMBERS?
WHO ELSE WILL BE PART OF THAT
ALLIANCE?
>> I CAN ONLY GUESS MAYBE
ANDREA.
>> NO.
>> I WOULD HOPE NOT BECAUSE WE
ALREADY SPOKE WITH HER.
>> WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON
HERE?
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW, THERE ARE
STILL CONVERSATIONS GOING ON BUT
IT SEEMS PRETTY CLEAR THAT
PHILLIP IS GOING TO BE THE ONE
TO GO.
YOU KNOW, OF COURSE, I COULD BE
BLINDSIDED.
I COULD BE VOTED OUT FIRST,
TWICE, WHICH WOULD BE THE WORST
THING EVER.
REALLY THE WORKFORCE THING
EVER-- I REALLY CAN'T TALK ABOUT
THAT POSSIBILITY RIGHT NOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW, DO YOU HAVE ANY
PREFERENCE OR INCLINATIONS OR
SOMETHING?
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
HOW ARE YOU THINKING YOU WANT TO
PLAY?
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE TO PLAY
WITH ME.
I JUST FEEL I DO TRUST YOU.
I FEEL LIKE ONE GOOD PERSON TO
TRUST IS GOING TO SAVE A LOT.
>> COMING INTO THIS GAME I WAS A
LITTLE BIT SKEPTICAL OF HOW DAWN
WOULD REACT TO ME BECAUSE I
ARGUABLY SCREWED HER OVER LAST
TIME.
I VOTED HER OUT.
I WASN'T SURE IF THERE WAS
ANYTHING TO BE ANY LINGERING
RESENTMENT.
I LIKE FRANCESCA.
I WAS HOPING--
>>Y DON'T TRUST FRANNIE FOR THE
LONG HAUL BECAUSE SHE'S GOING TO
PLAY TO WIN SO TO ME, SHE'S A
PERSON, TAKE OUT.
PHILLIP, MEDIUM.
>> I'M WILLING TO WORK WITH HER.
SHE'S HONEST TO A FAULT UNLESS
SHE'S REINVENTED HERSELF OVER
THE PAST YEAR AND DECIDED TO
PLAY A MORE CUTTHROAT GAME.
THE FACT THAT SHE IS WILLING TO
TAKE OUT FRANNIE WHO SHE
PROFESSED TO WORK WITH INDICATES
THIS IS A NEW DAWN.
MY CONVERSATION IS KIND OF WITH
THE OTHER FACTION OF, LIKE,
PHILLIP, ANDREA, YOU, ME,
MALCOLM.
>> I THINK THE TRUTH IS, IN THIS
GAME, IT'S NUMBERS.
>> IF IT'S ABOUT NUMBERS, THE
OTHER NUMBERS AREN'T SECURE.
>> I KNOW.
>> AS FAR AS I CAN TELL.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW-- I WANT
TO WORK WITH YOU.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S FAMILY FOR ME
TO TRUST.
YOU KNOW I'M GOOD THIS IS A
GAME.
COCHRAN AND I TALKED AT LENGTH
ABOUT STAYING TOGETHER AND
VOTING TOGETHER AND I TRUST HIM
RIGHT NOW AND WHAT I'M GOG HAVE
TO DO IS REALLY SEE WHAT'S IN
THE BEST INTEREST FOR US AS FAR
AS WHERE TO VOTE BECAUSE
WHEREVER COCHRAN AND I LIE WE
KIND OF SWING, AS FAR AS I CAN
TELL.
I MEAN, TO ME, IT'S PROBABLY THE
TIME FOR US TO SAY, LET'S TAKE
IT ALL THE WAY TO END AND LET'S
FIGURE OUT WHO THE OTHER PEOPLE
ARE.
>> WE HAVE TO COME TO A DECISION
RELATIVELY QUICKLY, THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
WHEW.
I WOULD LIKE USUL TO VOTE FOR
PHILLIP, BUT JUST IN CASE, I
DON'T KNOW IF WE NEED TO SPLIT
THE VOTE BETWEEN HIM AND
CORINNE.
>> YOU'RE SAYING CORINNE NEXT.
>> SHH.
I'M THINKING, JUST BECAUSE I
DON'T TRUST HER.
MALCOLM IS NOT TALKING UNLESS
HE'S TALKING TO ANY OF YOU GUYS.
>> THAT WOULD BE MALCOLM.
CORINNE, PHILLIP.
THAT'S ALL WE NEED.
>> BUT IF THEY HAVE AN IDOL,
THEY ONLY NEED THREE.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK IT IS WHY DO
YOU THINK THAT?
>> ONE OF THE THINGS WE'RE
CONSIDERING IS SPLITTING THE
VOTES BECAUSE AS UNLIKELY AS IT
MAY SEEM, IT IS POSSIBLE THAT
PHILLIP HAS AN IDOL, AND I HATE
TO, LIKE, GO DOWN THIS PARANOID
ROAD, BUT I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING DOES NOT FEEL RIGHT
ABOUT THE WAY THEY'RE BEHAVING.
>> SO NOW WHAT?
>> ANDREA KNOWS WE'RE SPLITTING
THE VOTE.
AND WHAT IF SHE TELLS .
>> FRAN TRUSTS HER.
>> WHO?
>> ANDREA.
I MEAN, THEY'RE CLOSE.
>> THAT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING
OUT HERE, DAWN.
>> I THINK FOR SURE CORAND I
KNOW ANDREA ARE TIGHT.
>> YOU'RE SKEPTICAL, TOO, I'M
GUESSING.
>> YEAH.
>> AND SO IS ERIK.
>> DAWN YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME.
I DON'T TRUST ANDREA AT ALL.
SHE'LL BE TALKING TO ONE PERSON
ONE SECOND, TALKING TO ANOTHER
PERSON THE NEXT.
STRATEGY, STRATEGY.
SHE'S STRATEGIC, DUDE.
SHE'S AWARE.
I'M MORE INTIMIDATED BY ANDREA
THAN ANYBODY ELSE OUT THERE.
I THINK FRAN HAS THE FENCE ON
ANDREA.
I DON'T KNOW ANDREA WELL.
IF SHE'S NERVOUS ABOUT IT, THEN
DO IT.
>> I JUST GOT A BAD VIBE FROM
HER, TOO.
>> THAT'S WHAT BRENDA SAID.
>> NO, GOD NO.
>> I NEED TO TALK TO HER.
>> LET'S TALK.
>> YOU TALK TO FRAN.
>> BRANDON AND ME JUST GOT A
REALLY WEIRD VIBE FROM ANDREA,
AND WE THINK SHE'S PLAYING BOTH
SIDES.
AND THAT SHE'S TELLING EVERYBODY
EVERYTHING AND SO WE JUST WANTED
THE SWITCH THE FIVE OF YOU, YOU,
BRENDA, AND DAWN AND NOT TELL
ANYBODY.
ANDREA AND COCK RAIN THINK WE'RE
SPLITTING THE VOTE BECAUSE THEY
COULD HAVE TOLD EVERYBODY THAT
WE'RE SPLITTING THE VOTE.
>> I TRUST COCHRAN.
>> YOU TRUST COCHRAN?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU TRUST ANDREA?
>> NO.
>> I DON'T TRUST HER AT ALL,
EITHER.
>> NOT 100%.
>> ERIK AND BRANDON SAID THEY
WANTED TO VOTE FOR ANDREA.
>> IT'S NOT ANYTHING AGAINST
HER, IT'S JUST THAT SHE IS SO
FREAKING SMART, DUDE.
>> OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
>> AND I'M JUST, LIKE, I MEAN,
AT THIS POINT, WE'RE LEAVING FOR
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I HAVE NO TIME TO TRY TO GET TO
THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
IF THAT'S WHAT THEY WANT TO DO,
THEN KNOW-- I MEAN, THE ONLY
REASON THEY CAME UP WITH THAT
PLAN IS BECAUSE I JUST DIDN'T
WANT US TO GET TOTALLY SCREWED,
AND NOW WE MIGHT-- THAT'S
EXACTLY WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN.
IF IT'S ME, I'M GOING TO BE
PISSED.
I'M GOING TO DROWN MYSELF IN THE
OCEAN.
>> OH, NO!
>> YOU KNOW, IN A WAY I WANT TO
VOTE OFF SOMEBODY LIKE
FRANCESCA.
THERE'S THIS KIND OF EMOTIONAL
ASPECT.
YOU CAN SAY YOU WANT TO PLAY THE
MOST STRATEGIC, COLD-BLOOD GAME
IN THE WORLD.
BUT EMOTIONS DO ENTER INTO THE
EQUATION.
THERE IS A PART OF ME THAT LIKES
HER.
IT SEEMS IMHUMANE.
I HAVE MORALS.
I HAVE A SENSE OF SHAME.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH,
APPROACH A FLAME, DIP IT IN AND
GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL, BECAUSE, AS YOU
GUYS KNOW, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR
LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
AND THAT IS GOING TO BE THE CASE
FOR ONE OF YOU TONIGHT.
BRANDON, IS SOMEBODY RUNNING
THIS TRIBE OR WHEN YOU HAVE 10
FAVORITES IS THERE REALLY NO
BOSS?
>> YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL KIND OF
CHIEFS.
THERE'S NO INDIANS HERE.
EVERYBODY IS, LIKE, THEIR OWN
PERSON.
NOBODY IS IT GOING TO GET DONE
LIKE THEY WERE DONE THE LAST
TIME.
>> Jeff: OH, SOMEBODY IS,
TONIGHT.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> WELL, NOW THAT YOU PUT IT
THAT WAY.
...
>> Jeff: SO, FRAN CHESK
ATHERE'S A COUPLE OF YOU GUYS
THAT PLAYED TOGETHER.
AND YOU PHILLIP WERE FAMOUS
BECAUSE OF YOUR RIVALRY BETWEEN
EACH OTHER.
AND THEN FOR THE WAY PHILLIP
WOULD CALL YOU FRAN-CHESK-QWA.
>> AND IT'S NEVER GOOD TO SEE
SOMEONE YOU HAD AN INFAMOUS
FIGHT WITH.
IT'S GOOD THAT HE LEARNED HOW TO
PRONOUNCE MY NAME.
>> FRANCESCA, FRANCESCA, FRAN
COMESKA.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Jeff: DID YOU WORK ON
SAYING THER NAME?
>> NO, ACTUALLY, I COULD IN FACT
SAY HER NAME BEFORE BUT DURING
THE COURSE OF THAT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THERE WERE CERTAIN
THINGS THAT WERE SAID, AND
RATHER THAN USE AN EXPLIKATIVE,
I DECIDED TO SAY FLAN-CHES-KWA.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, HOW WAS IT
FOR YOU TO SEE FRANCESCA?
>> SOMEWHAT APPREHENSIVE.
SOME OF THE SAME THINGS THAT
OCCURRED IN OUR SEASON, SHE WAS
VERY STRATEGIC EARLY ON IN THE
GAME WHEN SHE DIDN'T NECESSARILY
NEED TO BE SO I WAS CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT.
>> Jeff: FRANCESCA, PHILLIP'S
COMMENT BRINGS UP AN INTERESTING
POINT FOR YOU.
YOU ARE BACK FOR A SECOND
SEASON.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH
EXPERIENCE.
YOU WERE THE FIRST PERSON VOTED
OFF.
>> YOU KEEP BRINGING THAT UP,
JEFF.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE SAYING I'M BAD
AT "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: NO, I YOU SAID THAT.
>> THAT GUY IS GOOD.
>> Jeff: ALL I SAID ITS YOU
DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH EXPERIENCE.
>> ON THE ONE HAND YOU CAN LOOK
AT IT THAT WAY.
BUT EVERYBODY HERE IS SO SMART
AND KNOWS WHAT THEY'RE DOING
NOBODY FEELS SUPER SECURE.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN TONIGHT.
PLANS WERE CHANGING.
PEOPLE WERE GETTING PARANOID.
I MEAN, I GOT PARANOID.
AND WHAT'S THE PARANOIA STARTS
IT'S DEFINITELY LIKE A SNOWBALL
EFFECT.
>> I WANTED TO ADD, JEFF, SOME
SOMETIMES PARANOIA START WHEN
YOU HEAR THAT SOME PEOPLE
SUGGEST IT'S YOU.
>> Jeff: HAVE YOU HEARD YOUR
NAME TOSSED AROUND JAI HEARD MY
NAME TOSSED AROUND.
>> Jeff: ALREADY?
>> ALREADY.
>> WE WERE ALL PARANOID.
>> I THINK EVERYONE HERE.
YOU HEAR ONE LITTLE COMMENT, AND
YOU CAN JUST FREAK OUT.
IF YOU TELL THE WRONG THING TO
THE WRONG PERSON AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN IT GETS BACK TO YOU, AND
THEN MAYBE YOU WILL GO OUT.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK THE SAKE IT ON YOU FROM
THE OTHER NINE.
>> I THINK THEY SEE I BRING IT
TO CHALLENGES AND I DO WORK
AROUND CAMP BUT I'M NOT GOING TO
FEEL COMFORTABLE IN THIS GAME AT
ALL.
MY MISTAKE LAST TIME I PLAYED
WAS I GOT COMFORTABLE.
AND EVEN SOMETIMES WORKING
DISMARD BEING STRATEGIC OR
WORKING AROUND CAMP IT DOESN'T
REALLY MEAN ANYTHING.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, ONE OF THE
THINGS ABOUT PLAYING WITH
EXPERIENCED PLAYERS, GAME IS SO
MUCH FASTER.
THINGS CAN HAPPEN AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU CAN HAVE A PLAN IN PLACE,
AND SUDDENLY, HEAR SOMEBODY SAY
SOMETHING AND GO, "AH, WE GOTTA
CHANGE THINGS UP.
OF.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE'VE SEEN THAT HAPPEN BEFORE.
WE SAW BOSTON ROB REACH OUT HIS
HAND AND TOUCH THE SHOULDER OF
THE PERSON HE WANTED VOTED OFF.
THERE'S PRECEDENT FOR THIS.
ESPECIALLY ANY A GROUP OF
RETURNING PLAYERS, THERE ARE
CIRCLES WITHIN CIRCEPS AND
STRATEGIES AND BACKUP PLANS AND
THAT'S THE EXCITEMENT OF
RETURNING PLAYERS.
WE'RE NOT SPENDING THE FIRST
THREE DAYS, OH, MY GOD.
I HAVE TO GO TO A BATHROOM AND I
HAVE TO OPEN A COCONUT.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
IT'S EXCITING.
>> Jeff: WELL, SOMEBODY IS
ABOUT TO BE THE FIRST PERSON
VOTED OUT OF "FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES."
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
BRANDON, YOU'RE UP.
>> THIS IS A VOTE OUT OF
PARANOIA, BUT JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE PARANOID DOESN'T MEAN
SOMEONE ISN'T OUT TO GET YOU.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO BE SO UPSET
WITH ME.
BUT YOU'RE GETTING VOTED OUT
AGAIN FIRST BECAUSE YOU ARE A
HUGE THREAT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY TNOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ANDREA.
ANDREA.
THREE VOTES ANDREA.
FRANCESCA.
TWO VOTES FRANCESCA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES FRANCESCA,
THREE VOTES ANDREA.
ANDREA.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES ANDREA.
FRANCESCA.
WE'RE TIED.
FOUR VOTES ANDREA, FOUR VOTES
FRANCESCA.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES FRANCESCA,
FOUR VOTES ANDREA.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES," FRANCESCA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> Jeff: FRAN CHESK ATHE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
>> AGAIN.
>> Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, YOU ARE ONLY THREE DAYS
IN, BUT YOUR BIGGEST PROBLEM IS
THERE'S A GROUP OF FANS WHO KNOW
THEY CAN BEAT YOU.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO BE LOOKING
TO DO IT AGAIN SOON.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": BRANDON SEES HIS
LIFE IN THE GAME COMING TO AN
END.
>> WE'RE GETTING VOTED OUT.
I'M FEELING A LITTLE REVENGEFUL.
>> Jeff: AND RESURRECTS THE
HANS FAMILY REIGN OF TERROR.
>> I'M THINKING OF GOING RUSSELL
HANTZ STYLE.
I WANT TO GO OUT WITH A BANG.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> I CANNOT BELIEVE I GOT VOTE
THE OUT FIRST AGAIN.
I'M NOT GOING TO, LIKE, CRY
ABOUT IT, BUT I DID MAKE
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY AND THE GOOD
THING ABOUT BEING VOTED OUT
FIRST AGAIN SIKNOW HOW TO DEAL
WITH BEING VOTED OUT FIRST AND,
YOU KNOW, I GUESS I'M NOT CUT
OUT FOR "SURVIVOR."
IT'S OVER.
IT'S DONE.
I'M NO LONGER ROOTING FOR THE
FAVORITE.
NOW I'M ROOTING FOR THE FANS.