>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": FAVORITES HAVE A
HUGE LEAD.
DESPITE REYNOLD'S HEROICS
REYNOLD HAS MADE UP A LOT OF
GROUND!
THE FANS LOST THEIR THIRD
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IN A ROW.
FOR THE FAVORITES, WINNING
WASN'T THEIR PROBLEM.
THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE WAS
TARGETING ONE OF THEIR OWN.
>> SHE IS IN THE CORE SIX, BUT I
REALLY WANT CORINNE OUT.
>> Jeff: AND BRANDON HAD A
SERIES OF EMOTIONAL OUTBURSTS.
>> DON'T BE MEAN, BRANDON.
>> I'M BEING VICIOUS.
I'LL PEE IN THE RICE.
I'LL PEE IN THE BEANS.
I'LL BURN THE SHELTER TO THE
GROUND.
>> Jeff: THE ENTIRE TRIBE WAS
LEFT WONDERING WHAT HE WOULD DO
NEXT.
AT THE FANS CHAMP, SHAMAR WAS A
CONSTANT SOURCE OF CONFLICT.
>> SHUT UP!
>> Jeff: AND EVEN THREATENED
TO QUIT THE GAME.
>> WE WILL BE DOWN TWO IF YOU
QUIT.
>> Jeff: BUT IT WAS AN EYE
INJURY THAT ULTIMATELY SEALED
HIS FATE.
>> FROM MY PERSPECTIVE I WOULD
THRIEK PULL YOU FROM THE GAME.
>> Jeff: LOSING WAS TAKING ITS
TOTAL ON THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE.
>> TONIGHT'S TRIBAL IS
DEFINITELY BASED ON PHYSICAL
STRENGTH OR OUR LOYALTIES AND
OUR ALLIANCES.
>> I THINK TONIGHT IS THE
MAKE-OR-BREAK FACTOR FOR THIS
TRIBE.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
IN THE END, REYNOLD PLAYED IT
SAFE.
>> GOTTA DO IT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: AND THE FANS CHOSE TO
KEEP STRENGTH OVER LOYALTY.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES."
LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
15 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> YUP, I HEAR YOU.
I THINK WE MADE THE RIGHT
DECISION.
I FEEL REALLY GOOD ABOUT IT, AND
I'M HOPING YOU GUYS ARE FEEL THE
SAME WAY.
>> I FEEL GREAT.
>> I THINK NO HARD FEELINGS TO
LAURA.
SHE'S THE WEAKEST SWIMMER.
>> NO HARD FEELINGS FOR LAURA AT
ALL.
RIGHT NOW WE HAVE TO WIN
CHALLENGES AND--
>> THE GAME GOT SIMPLIFIED.
>> YUP.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, SHERRI?
>> I'M FINE.
>> YOU'RE AWFUL QUIET.
>> I'M JUST LISTENING.
WE VOTED OUT LAURA AND IT WAS A
REALLY HARD DECISION BECAUSE
LAURA-- LAURA IS SPECIAL TO ME.
SHE KIND OF REMINDED ME OF MY
DAUGHTER, I MEAN, A SWEET GIRL.
AND I DIDN'T WANT TO WRITE HER
NAME DOWN, BUT I HAD TO GO WITH
THE TRIBE BECAUSE THEY WERE ALL
GOING TO VOTE FOR HER NO MATTER
WHAT.
>> SO TONIGHT, YOUR IDOL GOT
FLUSHED.
>> FINE.
I THINK-- I THINK IT'S A GOOD
THING, HONESTLY, BECAUSE IT WAS
A-- A POINT OF DIVISION.
WHAT'S DONE IS DONE.
THE IDOL'S GONE.
WE'VE GOT THE SIX OF US.
>> I'M STILL NOT TRUSTING
ANYBODY FULLY BECAUSE TRIBAL ONE
AND TRIBAL, TWO I WENT IN WITH
ALL THESE HOPES AND ASPIRATIONS
AND BELIEVING THESE PEOPLE AND I
GOT COMPLETELY DUPED.
THIS LAST TRIBAL, I DECIDED
HOURS BEFORE I'M PLAYING THE
IDOL.
THIS IS MY FREE PASS.
I FOUND IT.
I EARNED IT.
I'M GOING TO SAY EXACTLY WHAT I
FEEL.
YOU GUYS ARE WORTHLESS IN
CHALLENGES.
YOU NEED ME IF YOU WANT TO WIN.
AND IF YOU DON'T KEEP ME AROUND,
YOU'LL MAYBE GET JUROR ONE OR
JUROR TWO AND IT FELT SO GOOD TO
JUST BE HONEST AND SAY IT, AND
IT WAS LIKE, BINGO!
HERE'S MY IDOL.
I DON'T CARE.
THAT WAS WORTH IT.
I HOPE YOU DON'T THINK I WAS
TAKING JABS AT YOU GUYS AND YOUR
AEXPLIENS MORE THAN YOU GUYS
TOOK JABS AT US AND OUR ALLIANCE
EARLY ON.
THAT'S THE GAME.
IST US TO JUST MOVE FORWARD
TOGETHER.
>> YOU KNOW, REYNOLD PLAYED HIS
IDOL AND HE KNEW, THERE'S, LIKE,
FIVE PEOPLE AGAINST EDDIE AND
REYNOLD.
SO, OF COURSE, YOU KNOW, HE'S
LIKE, "I'M GOING TO PLAY THE
IDOL."
NOW IT'S JUST KIND OF OUT HERE
ON THE ISLAND SOMEWHERE FOR
SOMEONE ELSE TO FIND.
>> WHOEVER WAKES UP FIRST IS
MAKING A FIRE.
>> IF I'M NOT WEAK, WILL YOU
WAKE ME UP.
>> ALL YOU'RE GOING TO DO IS
LOOK FOR THE IDOL AGAIN.
>> I STILL DON'T WANT REYNOLD TO
HAVE THE IDOL BECAUSE HE'S A
DANGEROUS PLAYER.
HE'S REALLY-- HE'S A CLUTCH GUY.
HE'S BEEN OUR CLUTCH MAN IN ALL
THE CHALLENGES.
HE'S CLUTCH WITH GETTING THE
FIRE STARTED.
HE CAN PULL THROUGH.
SO THAT'S WHY I DON'T WANT HIM
NEAR THE IDOL.
I DON'T WANT HIM PULLING THROUGH
AND FIGURING THIS THING OUT AND
GETTING HIMSELF TOO FAR AT MY
EXPENSE.
>> THE MOST REAL PEOPLE IN THE
WORLD HAVE REALLY, REALLY,
STRONG FEELING FEELINGS
EMOTIONS AND HAVE PASSION.
AND I HAVE SUCH A PASSION FOR MY
FAMILY.
I'D GIVE MY LIFE 1,000 TIMES IN
THE MOST HORRIFIC WAY JUST TO
SEE MY WIFE AND MY KIDS.
I STARTED THINKING ABOUT MY
FAMILY, MY WIFE AND MY KIDS AND
HOW MUCH THEY NEEDED ME AT HOME.
AND JUST LEAVING THEM AT THE
TROCH A HAT JUST TO PLAY A GAME.
I FELT LIKE I WAS BEING
COMPLETELY SELFISH, COMPLETELY
SELFISH.
I'M RESPONSIBLE FOR NOT ONLY MY
LIFE, BUT MY TWO BABIES, MY TWO
PRECIOUS BABIES THAT DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
THEY JUST THINK, HEY, DADDY'S GP
AGAIN.
I CAN'T DO THAT ANYMORE.
ENOUGH'S ENOUGH.
I'VE BEEN MISERABLE.
EVERY DAY IS A WASTE.
SO... NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL IF WE
HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I'M VOLUNTEERING FOR YOU TO VOTE
ME OUT OF THE GAME.
>> BRANDON BASICALLY TOLD US HE
WANTS TO GET OUT OF THIS GAME.
IMMEDIATELY MY MIND STARTS
REELING FROM THE IMPLICATIONS.
NOW MY TRIBE IS GOING TO LOSE A
MEMBER ON FORCE.
THIS HAS REPERCUSSIONS OUTSIDE
THE HANTZ FAMILY.
AND AS MUCH AS I DON'T WANT THAT
TO WEIGH ON HIS DECISION, MAYBE
HE SHOULD HAVE THOUGHT OF THAT
BEFORE HE DECIDED TO JUMP OUT
HERE WITH THE REST OF US.
>> IT REALLY HURTS MY PRIDE TO
HAVE TO, YOU KNOW, ADMIT ALL
THESE STUPID THINGS BUT I WAS
ABOUT TO LIGHT THE WHOLE THING
ON FIRE.
>> I'M GLAD YOU DIDN'T DO THAT.
WAY TO CHOOSE THE OTHER OPTION.
>> I WAS GOING TO PEE IN THE
BEANS AND RICE.
>> OKAY, I'M GLAD--
>> WE GNARLY ESCAPED THAT.
>> IT WAS A PETTY WAY OUT.
BUT, HEY, THOSE THINGS CROSSED
MY MIND.
MY APOLOGYS.
I'M SORRY FOR THE THOUGHT, I
AM--
>> IT'S OKAY.
IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
SO WE'RE ALL GOOD.
>> YEAH.
>> IT TURNS OUT BRANDON'S
ALTERNATIVE TO TELLING US HE WAS
GOING TO QUIT WAS HE GOING TO
BURN THE SHELTER DOWN AND/OR PEE
IN OUR BEANS AND RICE.
I WANT HIM OFF MY CAMP
IMMEDIATELY.
HE'S LOCO, FOR SURE.
CLEARLY, HE'S SPINNING OUT OF
CONTROL.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
AND IT'S A MATTER OF, LIKE, WHAT
DOES THAT MEAN FOR EVERYONE
AROUND HIM?
LIKE, WHAT'S HE GOING TO DO?
>> MY MOTIVATION TO COME OUT
HERE WAS MORE FOR SELFISH REASON
THANSZ MOTIVATED TO COME OUT
HERE FOR MY FAMILY.
BUT RATHER THAN LEAVE, I WANT TO
STAY HERE.
MY WHOLE PERSPECTIVE OF THE GAME
HAS COMPLETELY CHANGED.
I'M OUT HERE FOR THEM.
I'M GOING TO TOUGH IT OUT FOR
THEM.
I'M GOING TO DO THIS FOR THEM.
I HAD SOME TIME TO THINK AND
INSTEAD OF LEAVING, I'M GOING TO
GO OUT THERE AND I'M GOING TO
PLAY.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE THE MOST
INTENSE BRANDON YOU'VE SEEN THUS
FAR AND IT'S GOING TO BE
AWESOME.
I'M EXCITED.
I'M FREAKING MYSELF OUT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO
DO.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
FAVORITES GETTING YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW TRIBE OF FANS.
LAURA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, TWO MEMBERS OF EACH
TRIBE WILL HOLD ON TO A ROPE
WHICH IS ATTACHED TO A NET WHILE
MEMBERS OF THE OTHER TRIBE
ATTEMPT TO SHOOT COCONUTS INTO
THE NET.
THE MORE COCONUTS IN THE NET THE
HEAVIER IT BECOMES UNTIL YOU CAN
HOLD ON NO LONGER.
LAST TRIBE MEMBER HOLDING ON TO
THEIR NET WINS FOR THEIR TRIBE
REWARD.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL TAKE BACK TO CAMP WITH
THEM, BARBECUE.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: SAUSAGE.
STEAKS.
SOME VEGGIES.
SOME CONDIMENTS.
HAVE A LITTLE WINE TO GO WITH
IT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
YOU GUYS ARE SET.
>> Jeff: BIG REWARD.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES YOU HAVE
THREE EXTRA MEMBERS.
SITTING THREE PEOPLE OUT.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> COCHRAN--
>> I WANT TO SHOOT.
>> OKAY.
>> ANDREA, DAWN, AND ERIK ARE
SITTING OUT.
>> Jeff: TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH RIGHT DOWN THERE.
EVERYBODY ELSE, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
A ALL RIGHT, FOR THE FAVORITES,
WE HAVE PHILLIP AND BRANDON
HOLDING THE NET.
( APPLAUSE )
FOR THE FANS, WE HAVE MICHAEL
AND MATT HOLDING THE NET.
( APPLAUSE ).
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOUR JOB IS TO START PUTTING
COCONUTS INTO THE OTHER TRIBE'S
NETS, MAKE THEM HEAVY SO THEY
CAN'T HOLD ON TO THEM ANY
LONGER.
REYNOLD MAKES THE FIRST SCORE,
LANDS ONE IN BRANDON'S NET.
BRENDA SCORES ONE IN MICHAEL'S
NET.
SHERRY LANDS ONE FOR THE FANS.
EVERYBODY GETTING USE TOLD THE
WEIGHT AND HOW MUCH IT TAKES,
HOW MUCH EFFORT IT TAKES.
THOSE COCONUTS ARE HEAVY.
BIG REWARD.
FANS WOULD LIKE TO WIN A
CHALLENGE.
THE FAVORITES WOULD LIKE TO
CONTINUE TO DOMINATE AS THEY
HAVE THIS ENTIRE GAME.
PHILLIP HOLLERING SOME SORT OF
WAR CRY.
EDDIE COMES UP SHORT AGAIN.
JULIUS SCORES AGAIN.
SHERRI JUST MISSES.
CORINNE SCORES.
COCHRAN PUT ONE IN.
REYNOLD HASN'T MISSED YET.
HE'S ON FIRE!
>> BRANDON YOU'VE GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD IS PICKING ON
BRANDON, AND IT IS WORKING.
MATT NOW STARTING TO TAKE SOME
WEIGHT.
>> SHERRY YOU HAVE TO GO
FASTER.
>> Jeff: BRANDON TAKING A LOT
OF WEIGHT RIGHT NOW, STRUGGLING
TO HANG ON.
SHERRI IS WORTHLESS IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
REYNOLD AGAIN TRYING TO PICK ON
BRANDON A LITTLE MORE, AND HE
DOES.
BRANDON REALLY STRUGGLING TO
HANG ON.
MATT STRUGGLING HANG ON.
MICHAEL NOW STRUGGLING.
MALCOLM SCORES AGAIN.
BRENDA IS ON FIRE.
>> BRING IT?
>> YOU GOT TBRANDON!
>> Jeff: BRANDON IS OUT.
FAVORITES ARE DOWN TO ONE.
PHILLIP--
>> THIS IS ALL DAY THING.
>> PHILLIP, WE GOT YOU BABY.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM CONTINUES TO
PUMMEL MATT.
MATT IS HANGING IN THERE, BUT IT
IS TOUGH.
>> HANG ON, BABY!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM GIVES MATT
ANOTHER ONE.
HOW MUCH LODGER CAN HE HANG ON?
THE NOT AT ALL.
MATT IS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: IT IS PHILLIP AND
MICHAEL.
>> THIS IS AN ALL-DAY THING,
BABY!
>> Jeff: CORINNE PUTS ONE IN
MICHAEL'S.
MALCOLM WITH ANOTHER SHOT.
IT IS BACK AND FORTH.
>> PHILLIP, THIS IS NOTHING,
BABY.
COME ON, PHIL!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP STRUGGLING TO
HANG ON.
>> AIN'T NO STRUGGLE HERE.
>> Jeff: BRANDON WITH ANOTHER
HIT.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY!
YOU'RE STRONG.
>> COME ON!
>> STAY STRONG, BABY.
>> HOLD IT!
>> Jeff: MICHAEL RELEASES FOR
THE FANS!
FAVORITES WIN REWARD!
PHILLIP ONCE AGAIN THE HERO FOR
THE FAVORITE TRIBE.
>> YEAH, BABY!
I KNEW IT!
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES,
CONGRATULATIONS.
COME GET YOUR REWAR.
FANS, DESPITE ANOTHER GOOD
EFFORT, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
DEFINITELY TODAY I THOUGHT WAS
GOING TO BE A TURNAROUND FOR US.
I THOUGHT TODAY'S CHALLENGE WAS
MOST DEFINITELY OUR CHANCE TO
WIN, OUR CHANCE TO TURN IT
AROUND, GET THE TRIBE GOING IN
THE RIGHT DIRECTION, AND WE BLEW
IT.
WE NEED TO TRY SOMETHING NEW.
>> WE NEED TO TRY SOMETHING NEW.
>> YEAH.
>> WE NEED TO TRY SOMETHING NEW
AROUND THIS CAMP.
WE NEED TO TRY SOMETHING NEW AT
THE CHALLENGES.
>> IT IS SO HARD TO KEEP MY
MOUTH SHUT RIGHT NOW.
I WENT WITH YOUR PLAN AND I GOT
RID OF LAURA.
WE STILL LOST TODAY.
MUSCLE'S NOT PAYING OFF.
AND I JUST HOPE THE ALLIANCE
REALIZES THIS AND DOESN'T LISTEN
TO ALL THEIR CRAP ABOUT HOW WE
NEED MUSCLE.
WE NEED MUSCLE.
BUT WHO BEES?
NOW THE FEAR IS THE IDOL IS BACK
IN PLAY.
IT'S AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
I'VE GOT TO FIND IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> I DEFINITELY DON'T THINK IT'S
A BIG SECRET THAT EVERYONE'S
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
I MEAN, IT WAS FLUSHED OUT LAST
NIGHT.
I KNOW IT'S BACK ON THIS ISLAND
SOMEWHERE.
IT CAN'T BE THAT HARD TO FIND
BECAUSE REYNOLD FOUND IT PRETTY
QUICK.
USUALLY THE IDOL IS IN A TREE OR
UNDER A ROCK OR SOMETHING.
OH!
THAT SO LOOKED LIKE IT!
>> I DEFINITELY WANT TO FIND THE
IDOL, AND IF I FIND THE IDOL,
I'M NOT TELLING ANYBODY IN THIS
TRIBE.
>> I'M TOTALLY FOLLOWING MY
INSTINCTS OF WHERE THE IDOL
COULD BE.
I MEAN, USUALLY IT'S BY
SOMETHING UNIQUE OR, LIKE, A
WEIRD TREE OR A WEIRD ROCK IS
OUT OF PLACE, JUST SOMETHING
THAT KIND OF STANDS OUT.
>> THINGS ARE JUST SO CRAZY, YOU
NEVER KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
WE'RE DOWN IN NUMBERS, AND
PEOPLE ARE FIDGETY, AND I WANT
TO KNOW WHERE IT IS.
AND IF IT'S?
MY POCKET, IT'S SO IMPORTANT.
IT CAN TAKE ME SO MUCH FURTHER
IF I CAN FIND IT, AND AS LONG AS
REYNOLD DOESN'T FIND IT.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO FIND IT.
>> TWICE!
TWICE!
NUMBER TWO!
OH, MY GOD!
"CONGRATULATIONS, YOU FOUND
FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL."
I KNOW ALL THIS BY HEART.
IT'S THE SECOND ONE I FOUND.
I MEAN, I MIGHT AS WELL JUST
KEEP PLAYING THEM IF I CAN JUST
KEEP FINDING THEM.
BUT I DON'T WANT THE MAJORITY
ALLIANCE TO KNOW I HAVE THE IDOL
BECAUSE WHEN THEY FOUND OUT I
HAD IT LAST TIME THEY STARTED
GUNNING FOR ME IN ORDER TO FLUSH
IT OUT.
I DON'T WANT IT TO GET FLUSHED.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO USE IT FOR
A TIME WHEN IT WILL REALLY MAKE
A BIG DIFFERENCE, AND I THINK
THERE'S A DIRECT CORRELATION
BETWEEN OPENING YOUR BIG, FAT
MOUTH AND THE IDOL HAVING TO GET
PLAYED.
MOUTH SHURKT BUT EDDIE'S MY BOY
TO THE END.
I'LL PROBABLY TELL EDDIE.
BACK IN BUSINESS, BABY.
THIS IS HOW YOU PLAY "SURVIVOR."
EDDIE.
YOU AND ME TAKING THIS THING TO
THE END?
>> HOPING.
>> I GOT IT.
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> REALLY?
>> REALLY.
>> IT'S IN MY BAG.
>> THAT'S AWESOME, DUDE.
>> SO WE GOT ONE MORE INSURANCE
POLICY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND YOU ME, DUDE.
ALL THE WAY.
>> ALL THE WAY.
>> I MEAN, YOU CAN'T GET ANY
LUCKIER THAN THAT.
YOU CAN'T.
YOU GET RID OF IT AND SIX HOURS
LATER YOU HAVE IT AGAIN.
THAT'S AWESOME.
THE FUNNIEST PART OF THE WHOLE
THING SHERRI'S WANTED THIS IDOL
SINCE DAY ONE, AND EVEN TODAY
SHERRI IS WALKING AROUND COMBING
THE BEACH EVERYWHERE, COMBING
THE WOODS, LOOKING FOR THIS
IDOL, AND IT'S JUST FUNNY TO
WATCH.
>> WHOA!
HOLY STEAK!
THOSE ARE THICK STEAKS.
>>> BRANDON, THANK YOU FOR DOING
THAT.
>> BRANDON SEEMED SULLEN.
THERE'S SOMETHING IN HIS EYES.
YOU CAN TELL HE'S GOING BACK AND
FORTH IN HIS OWN MIND.
I HOPE THIS WIN BROUGHT HIS
SPIRITS UP, BUT WE'VE BEEN ON A
WINNING STREAK SO I DON'T EVEN
KNOW IF HE WON THE MILLION
DOLLARS IF HE WOULD EVER GET
RIGHT IN HIS HEAD.
>> YOU GUYS WERE SO STRONG.
EVERYBODY-- I MEAN, EVERY
PERSON.
>> BRANDON, YOU WERE A ROCK.
THAT'S THE REASON IT WORKED.
>> YOU WERE THE MAN THERE AT THE
END.
>> I HAD STRATEGY, TOO.
I KEPT YELLING AT THEM.
WHEN I PLAYED BASKETBALL--
>> I WAS TRYING SO HARD NOT TO
MAKE THIS GAME ABOUT ME ANYMORE,
AND HE ALL OF A SUDDEN DECIDES
TO TAKE OWNERSHIP OF WINNING THE
CHALLENGE BY HIMSELF.
PHILLIP SHEPPARD, THIS
DUMB-ASS SPIKE, AGENT-- WHATEVER
YOU YOU WANT TO CALL HIM--
THINKS HE WON THE CHALLENGE AND
IT REALLY, REALLY, REALLY PISSES
ME OFF I DON'T WANT TO HEAR THAT
CRAP.
RIGHT NOW I'M A LITTLE BIT
AGGRAVATED AND I FEEL LIKE
VENTING A LITTLE BIT.
>> PHIL ARE, WE TAKING THIS
DOWN?
>> NO I WANT TO SAVE MY ENERGY
FOR THE CHALLENGES.
I WANT TO KEEP WINNING
CHALLENGES.
I DON'T WANT TO DECONSTRUCT THIS
YET AGAIN.
HOW MANY TIMES DO WE HAVE TO DO
THIS?
>> SHE WAS JUST MAKING A
SUGGESTION, PHILLIP.
>> I KNOW, AND I'M GIVING MY
INPUT AS WELL.
>> BE HONEST, PHILLIP, YOUR
INPUT IS MORE, YOU KNOW,
DICTATORSHIP KIND OF ATTITUDE.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S NICE.
>> I JUST SAID I THINK WE SHOULD
LEAVE IT.
>> YOU SAY A LOT EVERY TIME
SOMEBODY SAYS SOMETHING.
>> BUT I WILL ARGUE WITH YOU,
PHILLIP.
>> THEN ARGUE.
BUT IT WILL BE A ONE-SIDED
CONVERSATION.
>> HOW ABOUT YOU SHUT THE
( BLEEP ) UP AND LET SOMEBODY
ELSE HAVE AN OPINION.
>> I THINK WE CAN ALL AGREE
BRANDON IS DEFINITELY UNSTABLE
AND UNPREDICTABLE.
WHAT ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO DO WITH
THAT?
IT'S JUST-- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
DO WITH IT.
>> BRANDON FINALLY SNAPPED.
PHILLIP DIDN'T DO ANYTHING OUT
OF THE ORDINARY, BUT HE CAUGHT
BRANDON IN ONE WERE HIS DOWNWARD
SWINGS, AND FOR ME, NO MATTER
WHAT STRATEGIC CONSIDERATION
BRANDON PLAYS, AT SOME POINT,
HE'S GOING TO GO PAST THRESHOLD,
WHERE HE'S MORE OF A DRAIN ON
THE CAMP THAN HE'S GOING TO BE
USEFUL DOWN THE ROAD.
>> YOU ALL THINK I SHOULD GO
APOLOGIZE TO HIM?
>> I'D WAIT A DAY OR TWO.
>> YEAH, I DON'T THINK HE'S
GOING TO TOUCH IT NOW.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE SOME
YOUNG PUNK TELLING ME TO SHUT
UP.
HE JUST DIDN'T KNOW.
I'M A STREET FIGHTER.
I DON'T WANT TO GET INVOLVED IN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I'M TRYING EVERYTHING I CAN TO
AVOID THAT, BUT IF HE EVER CAME
AT ME, HE'S GOING TO SEE A
DIFFERENT SIDE OF ME.
I THINK HE'S UNSTABLE AND I
THINK HE SHOULD BE OUT OF THE
GAME.
IF THEY WANT TO KEEP HIM IN THE
GAME, THEY CAN KEEP HIM IN THE
GAME BUT I WILL PLAY A DIFFERENT
GAME.
>> LET'S TALK.
>> NO, I WANT TO SAY THIS TO
YOU, MY DILEMMA, WITH ME, THE
WAY I TRIED TO PLAY IT RIGHT
NOW, I TOLD YOU, YOU WERE GOING
TO GET ABOVE WHERE YOU FINISHED
LAST TIME.
YOU DON'T SLAPT GIFT HORSE.
>> IN OTHER WORDS YOU DON'T BITE
THE HAND THAT FEEDSES--
>> EXACTLY.
I'M TELLING EVERYBODY, NO, NO,
HE DESERVES TO BE HERE.
>> WHAT GIVES YOU THE LEADERSHIP
TO SAY, "HEY, HE DESERVES TO BE
HERE."
DON'T I MAKE THAT DECISION FOR
MYSELF?
>> YOU MISSED A CLOSE CALL.
>> SO I CAN STILL TRUST YOU.
>> YES, YOU CAN TRUST ME.
I'VE BEEN TELLING YOU THAT.
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN ANNOYED WITH
PHILLIP.
I'VE LISTENED TO HIM.
I'VE KISSED HIS BUTT, BUT AT THE
SAME TIME I HAVE TO KEEP MYSELF
UNDER CONTROL.
AND AS LONG AS I CAN KEEP MYSELF
UNDER CONTROL, I'LL BE GOOD.
BUT BY DAMN, THAT MIGHT BE A
REALLY TOUGH THING TO DO.
I APOLOGIZE AS A MAN.
>> HEY, MAN, I'M SORRY.
I HOPE WE'RE OKAY.
AM I STILL-- NO, YOU'RE NOT.
IN MY BOOK YOU'RE PERSONA
NONGRATTA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO PLAY THE GAME.
THE FIRST OPPORTUNITY I HAVE TO
GET HIM OUT OF THE GAME HE WILL
GO.
I'M NOT GOING TO PUT UP WITH IT
ANYMORE.
THAT WHEN THE SUN DOES APPEAR,
EVERYTHING IS READY TO DRY.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO DO
ANYTHING.
MY FEET ARE JUST JACKED.
>> I'VE BEEN WET FOR, LIKE, TWO
DAYS STRAIGHT.
AND MY FEET JUST LOOK LIKE A
DEAD PERSON'S FEET.
I CAN BARELY MOVE MY TOES, AND
IT FEELS LIKE I'M ON NAILS
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET OUT OF
THIS SITUATION BY SITTING IN THE
HUT, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S MY THOUGHT.
>> CAMP LIFE AT GOTA HAS BEEN A
LONG STRAND OF HELL.
WE'RE FAILING ON ALL LEVELS OF
SURVIVOR, BUT WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, WE CAN'T JUST WALLOW
UNDER THE PALM FRONDS AND HOPE
THAT EVERYTHING IS GOING TO GET
BETTER BECAUSE IT'S NOT.
( THUNDER )
>> OH, GOD!
>> IT'S BEEN RAINING FOR ALMOST
48 HOURS STRAIGHT NOW.
I HAVE A DEFINITE HEAD COLD.
I KNOW THAT FAIR FACT.
ALL MY CLOTHES ARE WET.
EVERYTHING I HAVE BEEN SLEEPING
IN IS WET.
IT JUST SUCKS.
>> THE FIRE, DOES IT HAVE ANY
CHANCE?
>> THAT'S THE BEST I CAN DO.
>> OKAY.
THE JOKE IS UP.
WE'RE ALL IN A HOLLYWOOD STUDIO.
TURN OFF THE WIND EFFECTS,
PLEASE
>> THIS SUCKS!
I WANT MY MOMMY!
A LOT OF BAD THINGS HAVE HAMMOND
OVER THE LAST 13 DAYS.
I TRY TO BE AS STRONG AS
POSSIBLE, BUT THERE'S DEFINITELY
TIMES WHEN YOU'RE SO HUNGRY,
YOU'RE SO COLD AND SO THIRSTY
THAT YOU FEEL LIKE, GOD!
I WISH SOMETHING GOOD WOULD
HAPPEN TO OUR TRIBE.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> THIS PHILLIP AND BRANDON
RIVALRY, IT'S GETTING TO ME.
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING, WHO
STARTS THE FIRE?
BRANDON STARTS THE FIRE.
WHO'S THE ONLY DUDE IN THIS
TRIBE WHO CAN START A FIRE WITH
A PIECE OF FLINT?
BRANDON.
SO I DON'T NEED NO OLD
54-YEAR-OLD PUNK BITCH TELLING
ME DON'T BITE THE HAND THAT
FEEDS YOU.
HE DOESN'T FEED ME.
I'M A HANTZ.
I FEED ME.
>> TREE MAIL, EVERYBODY.
>> "TODAY THE TRIBES WILL BE'
BOXING' YOU'LL FIGHT FOR YOUR
LIFE IN THE GAME.
NO TIME FOR A COMMUNICATION
BREAKDOWN.
TONIGHT ANOTHER WILL LOSE THEIR
FLAME."
>> WE'VE GOT TO GET BRANDON OUT
OF CAMP.
HE'S NOT SANE.
HE'S NOT RIGHT.
HE COULD HARM ONE OF UTS AND,
THEREFORE, SOMETIMES YOU MIGHT
DO THE UNTHINKABLE TO MAKE
SOMETHING ELSE POSSIBLE.
I WOULD NORMALLY NEVER CONSIDER
THROWING A CHALLENGE.
I'M TOO MUCH A COMPETITOR.
BUT IN THIS INSTANCE, THE GOOD
OUTWEIGHS THE BAD.
IT IS A DEGREE OF COMPASSION FOR
HIM, AS WELL AS IT IS
POTENTIALLY A GAME SAVER FOR US
BY ELIMINATING HIM OUT OF THE
GAME, BY THROWING A CHALLENGE.
CHALLENGE.
>> WHAT HAPPENS?
>> HE NEEDS TO GO.
I WANT HIM GONE.
PUT ME IN THE CHALLENGE.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO THROW THE
CHALLENGE?
>> YES, I WOULD DO THAT.
I DON'T WANT HIM AROUND ME
ANYMORE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HE NEEDS TO GO.
IF HE DOESN'T GO, I'M NOT GOING
TO BE HAPPY.
DO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
I CAN'T SEEM TO HAVE A PRIVATE
CONVERSATION WITH ANYBODY.
IT'S CALLED A ONE-ON-ONE.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
( SIGHS )
>> I APOLOGIZED.
I WAS THE BIGGER MAN ABOUT IT.
>> I THOUGHT YOU GUYS WORKED IT
OUT.
>> I DID.
LITERALLY, EVERYTHING WAS FINE.
>> HEY, PHILLIP.
>> I DON'T LIKE WHERE THIS IS
GOING.
>> IS HE WANTING TO THROW THE
CHALLENGE?
>> I DON'T THINK HE'S GOING THAT
FAR.
I'M JUST SAYING, IF WE LOSE,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE ISSUES
>> I'M STARTING TO BOIL A LITTLE
BIT, BOIL A LITTLE BIT.
MAN!
FOR SOMEONE WHO COOKS, WHO DOES
GOOD IN CHALLENGES, WHO KEEPS
THE FIRE UP EVERY NIGHT, PRETTY
MUCH TAKES CARE OF CAMP--
PHILLIP, CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A
SECOND?
AND HE STILL WANTS TO GET ME
VOTED OUT.
WE SQUASHED THIS.
I THOUGHT WE FIGURED THIS OUT
YESTERDAY.
>> FIGURED OUT WHAT.
>> OUR AGREEMENT TO SQUASH THIS.
>> SO WHAT IS YOUR MIND TELLING
YOU NOW IS THERE YOU'RE MAKING A
SUPPOSITION.
YOU'RE SUPPOSING SOMETHING.
>> NO, ANDREA SPOKE TO ME AND
SAID THAT YOU STILL WANT ME
VOTED OUT.
>> WELL, I'M NOT HAPPY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED WITH US.
AND YOU SAID TO ME YESTERDAY, "I
CAN TRUST YOU?"
AND THAT'S A VERY REAL CONCERN
FOR YOU.
FOR ME, I'M NOT SURE I CAN TRUST
YOU.
YOUR ACTIVITIES HAVE BEEN PRETTY
ACTIVE.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE BEEN SHARING
INFORMATION WITH OTHER PEOPLE.
AISE TOLD YOU WHEN I PUT YOU IN
STEALTH "R" US, ONE OF OUR
REQUIREMENTS FOR DOING THAT--
>> CAN YOU DROP THE STEALTH "R"
US THINGS.
IT'S LIKE PLAYING WAY CHILD.
IT'S DEMEANING MAN.
>> IT'S TRUE.
>> I'M NOT CONQUEROR, NOBODY IN
THERE IS EXTERMINATOR AND
EXTERIOR.
IT'S BULL.
>> IT'S A LOT OF FUN FOR US.
>> IT'S NOT.
NOBODY LIKES IT.
NOBODY LIKES THEIR ( BLEEP )
NAME.
>> THANK YOU FOR SHARING THAT.
>> EVERYBODY ACTUALLY DOESN'T
LIKE YOU.
>> THEN GUESS WHAT, THEY'LL VOTE
ME OUT.
>> BRANDON!
NO!
>> NO!
BRANDON!
>> COME ON, BRANDON!
>> BRANDON, OUT NOW!
>> STOP IT!
>> HEY, PHIL!
HERE'S A REASON TO VOTE ME OUT
YOU LITTLE ( BLEEP ).
WITH YOUR STEALTH "R" US
( BLEEP ), HUH.
COME ON, BITCH!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE A SECRET
AGENT!
COME GET SOME!
COME ON!
>> PICK UP THE LITTLE BITS THAT
ARE STILL CLEAN.
>> NOW, VOTE ME OUT, BITCH!
>> HEY.
JUST GIVE YOURSELF SOME TIME TO
BREATHE.
>> HE'S NOT GOING TO DISRESPECT
ME ANYMORE.
>> GIVE YOURSELF SOME TIME TO
BREATHE.
>> I'M THE AUTHOR OF MY FATE,
BUDDY!
I'M THE AUTHOR OF MY FATE!
NOW VOTE ME OUT, BITCH!
>> WHY WASN'T ONE EFFECTIVE
ENOUGH?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HE DID THAT.
>> WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
( CRYING )
>> BRANDON IS READY TO FIST
FIGHT.
HE'S LITERALLY OUT OF HIS MIND.
>> WHY DON'T WE JUST NOT GO TO
THE CHALLENGE?
>> I THINK IN THIS CASE--
>> LET'S GO TO TRIBAL.
>> THERE'S SO MUCH TO CONSIDER
WHEN SOMETHING LIKE THAT
HAPPENS.
WE'RE TRYING TO DECIDE IS HE IN
A PLACE AT ALL WHERE WE CAN
STILL PLAY WITH HIM, FORFIT THE
CHALLENGE, GIVE IMMUNITY AWAY,
WHICH YOU NEVER DO IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
REYNOLD, YOU HAD A LONG, WET,
RAINY NIGHT LAST NIGHT.
WHAT'S THE IMPACT ON THE TRIBE?
>> WELL, I MEAN, I GUESS IT'S A
TESTAMENT TO HOW HARD THIS GAME
REALLY IS.
LIKE, FROM OUR POINT OF VIEW,
YOU GUYS ARE WINNING THE
REWARDS.
YOU GUYS HAVE THIS PLUSH SHELTER
WITH THE TARP AND YOUR ROCKING
CHAIRS AND PILLOWS AND STEAK
DINNERS AND YOU'RE DRINKING YOUR
BOTTLES OF WINE AND HAVING A
GOOD OLD TIME, AND WHAT IT BOILS
DOWN TO IS THIS GAME IS
EXTREMELY HARD EVEN IF YOU WIN
EVERY SINGLE CHALLENGE.
NOBODY IS IMMUNE FROM THE
ELEMENTS.
IN A SENSE, WE'RE ALL IN THIS
TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN FATIGUE SETS IN TO THE MOOD
AND THE MORAL.
>> IT DAMAGES MORAL.
YOU FEEL TIRED.
YOU FEEL WORSE.
YOU GET A LITTLE GRUMPY.
IT RUBS OFF ON OTHER PEOPLE.
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR ANYBODY.
>> Jeff: BRANDON, HOW ARE YOU
DOING?
>> NOT DOING TOO WELL, JEFF.
HAD A LITTLE OUTBURST THIS
MORNING WITH PHILLIP, ACTUALLY.
AND I KIND OF WANTED TO TALK TO
THE OTHER TRIBE.
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
>> Jeff: YEAH.
>> LET ME STEP OFF MY MAT.
>> GUYS.
TONIGHT IS GOING TO BE A LITTLE
BIT DIFFERENT.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO HAVE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO COME BACK AND
MAKE THIS A GAME.
SO YOU GET A SECOND CHANCE, AND
I'M YOUR SECOND CHANCE.
SO PHILLIP, PLEASE DON'T LET
THIS GUY GET TO THE END OF THE
GAME.
PLEASE DON'T LET HIM GET TO THE
END OF THE GAME.
>> WHAT OF WHERE-- WHERE ARE YOU
GOING?
>> JEFF, I'D LIKE TO SAY
SOMETHING ON BEHALF OF THE
FAVORITES IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE REALIZE THAT THIS IS GOING TO
BE A CHALLENGE FOR IMMUNITY, AND
IT'S FOR THAT REASON THAT WE'RE
GOING T TO FORFEIT THE CHALLENGE
THAT WE MAY GO TO TRIBAL.
WHILE WE'RE ALL FIERCE
COMPETITORS, WE HAVE DISCOURSE
IN OUR CAMP AND WOULD LIKE TO
HASH THAT OUT IN THE APPROPRIATE
SETTING.
WE RESPECT THIS GAME AND WE HOPE
YOU AND THE FANS CAN RESPECT OUR
DECISION TO GO TO TRIBAL.
>> LET ME HELP YOU OUT A LITTLE
BIT.
THEY DON'T RESPECT ANYTHING
ABOUT THE FANS.
THAT'S BULL( BLEEP ), CORINNE.
COMPLETE BULL.
>> OKAY, BRANDON.
>> DON'T PLAY THIS I'M COOL WITH
THE FANS, PERIOD.
THIS IS A FIRST TIME PLAYING AND
YOU DESERVE A CHANCE, AND A FAIR
CHANCE.
DON'T TAKE CRAP FROM ANYBODY.
YOU'RE THE UNDERDOG.
I LOVE THE UNDERDOG.
I WAS AN UNDERDOG, TOO.
AND I STILL AM --
>> BRANDON, BRANDON, COME OVER
HERE.
>> YEAH, SLIEWBLGTHS.
>> Jeff: YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
A LITTLE-- LIKE YOU'RE STUCK IN
BETWEEN THIS WORLD SO COME OVER
HERE IN A NEUTRAL SPOT.
>> I LIKE THIS SPOT.
>> Jeff: OKAY, SO, BRANDON,
TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON OVER
HERE.
YOU COME OUT HERE AND SAY,
"LISTEN, I'M GOING TO HELP YOU
FANS OUT."
EXPLAIN WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
>> PHILLIP OVER HERE DECIDES TO
MAKE THIS LITTLE STEALTH "R" US
A NAME, GIVES EVERYBODY A
CARTOON NAME, DEGRADING US,
MAKING US FEEL LIKE WE'RE
FREAKING PLASTIC DOLLS.
I'M NOT DOWN FOR THAT.
AND PHILLIP SPEAKS SO HIGHLY OF
HIMSELF.
STOP TALKING ABOUT YOURSELF.
BOSTON ROB TOOK YOU TO THE END
OF THE GAME.
YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
YOU WERE MADE FUN OF, AND YOU
COME HERE AND YOU TELL ME DON'T
BITE THE HAND THAT FEEDS YOU!
I FEED MYSELF.
YOU DON'T DO JACK FOR ME.
SO YOU AIN'T GOING TO TELL ME
YOU'RE RUN, THE GAME.
I TOOK MYSELF OUT OF THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: BRANDON, SO NOW HOW
ARE YOU FEELING RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE ARE YOU CLEARLY --
>> FIRED UP, BRO.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE CLEARLY FIRED
UP.
YOU SEEM A LITTLE HOSTILE.
>> JUST A TAD.
>> Jeff: BUT I'M A LITTLE
CONCERNED ABOUT THAT, BUT WE'LL
CONSTITUENT HERE AND TALK
THROUGH IT.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE
FRUSTRATED WITH YOUR TRIBE AND
THERE ARE SOME SPECIFIC
INCIDENTS, BUT THAT IS PART OF
"SURVIVOR" AND YOU'RE USED TO
THAT.
>> I HAD A ROUGH TIME AFTER THE
SHOW.
I HAD A REALLY ROUGH TIME.
>> Jeff: AFTER THE FIRST TIME
YOU PLAYED "SURVIVOR."
>> AFTER THE FIRST TIME I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR" IT CHANGED MY
PERSONAL LIFE AND CHANGED
EVERYTHING AND I SWORE IF I GOT
A CHANCE TO PLAY AGAIN I WOULD
NEVER PLAY THE SAME DAY WAYPIM
WOULD NEVER BE THE GUY TO GET
WALKED OVER BY EPISODE, BY
EPISODE, BY EPISODE, CRYING.
I CAN STAND HERE PROUDLY TODAY
AND SAY I NEVER CRIED A
( BLEEP ) TEAR ON THIS SEASON.
I CALLOSSED MYSELF TO PEOPLE WHO
REALLY DON'T GIVE A ( BLEEP ).
THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT ANYBODY
BUT THEMSELVES.
THAT'S PATHETIC, AND YOU'RE
GOING NOWHERE IN WITH THAT
ATTITUDE, IN LIFE OR IN
"SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, GIVE ME SOME
INSIGHT FROM THE OTHER SIDE.
YOU HAVEN'T ACTUALLY MADE ANY
REACTION DURING THIS EBB TIRE
TIRADE.
>> I AM, JEFF, FROM THE--
>>
( IMITATING PHILLIP )
>> I ATTEMPTED TO EMBRACE
BRANDON AND HE WOULD SAY,
"PHILLIP.
WHERE I DO STAND?
CAN I BE A PART OF THE ALLIANCE?
THIS IS AFTER HE DECIDED TO CAST
VOTES FOR ANDREA AT THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: SORRY TO INTRURNGHT
PHILLIP.
NOW, ANDREA, YOU'RE EMOTIONAL.
WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
>> FOR ME IT'S JUST-- IT'S JUST
REALLY HURTS-- IT'S SAD TO SEE--
I'VE GROWN CLOSE TO BRANDON OUT
HERE, AND I CAN'T RELATE TO WHAT
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH.
AND IT'S HARD BECAUSE WE'RE ALL
OUT HERE TO PLAY A GAME, AND
WE'VE BEEN DOING SO WELL, AND WE
HAD GREAT UNITY AND TO SEE TWO
PEOPLE FIGHT AND SAY REALLY
CRUEL THINGS TO EACH OTHER, IT
REALLY--
>> I SAID NOTHING TO BRANDON.
>> OKAY, OKAY, SORRY, THEN I'M
TALK AGO.
>> PHILLIP SHEPPARD DOESN'T SAY
NOTHING WRONG, EVER.
HE'S SUPER SPY AGENT.
3.0.
SHUT UP.
SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
OWN UP TO WHAT YOU DO.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE 100 YEARS
OLD DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVEN'T
MADE A MISTAKE I CAME AND
APOLOGIZE TO YOU.
>> OVER AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
YOU'RE ONE PATHETIC INDIVIDUAL.
>> YOU'RE PATHETIC.
>> SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
I'M TIRED OF YOU TALKING.
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING--
>> DON'T WALK THIS WAY.
>> Jeff: BRANDON.
BRANDON.
COME HERE, COME HERE.
I BROUGHT YOU OVER HERE FOR A
REASON I BROUGHT YOU HERE FOR A
REASON.
NOBODY WANTS TO GET PHYSICAL.
THAT'S NOT GOOD NEWS.
>> HE DOESN'T WANT TO GET
PHYSICAL.
>> YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I DON'T.
I REALLY, REALLY DON'T.
>> Jeff: I DON'T WANT YOU TO
GET PHYSICAL, ALL RIGHT.
HEY, LOOK AT ME.
>> I'M.
>> Jeff: NO, NO.
>> I'M DOING THIS FOR YOU, JEFF.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE DOING THIS FOR
ME?
>> I'M NOT DOING --
>> OH, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET
PHYSICAL FOR ME.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT ME RIGHT NOW
SAY YOU WILL NOT GET PHYSICAL.
OKAY.
DAUN, YOU ARE CAUTIOUSLY
BREATHING IN AND OUT TRYING TO
CALM YOUR BODY.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE HERE.
IT'S TOO STRESSFUL.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ALL THE
NEGATIVE.
I'M IN A GAME RIGHT NOW, TAKING
ME OUT OF IT.
>> DAWN, I LOVE YOU, I LOVE YOU
WITH ALL MY HEART.
YOU KNOW, I DO.
ANDREA, I LOVE YOU.
BUT I WANT TO BE THE AUTHOR OF
MY FATE IN THIS GAME.
AND THIS WAS MY THOUGHT PROCESS
AND I WAS TALKING TO FILL.
AND I SAID WHAT'S WRONG, MAN?
I WAS TRYING TO BE COOL.
THEN I CLICKED.
>> AND SAID YOU KNOW WHAT, SINCE
YOU GUYS AREN'T EATING, WE'RE
NOT GOING TO EAT, EITHER.
SO I TOOK THE RICE AND DUMPED IT
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
I TOOK THE BEANS AND DUMPED IT
SO NOW YOU CAN STARVE WITH THEM.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT THE WHOLE
TRIBE DESERVES THAT.
>> Jeff: CORINNE?
>> .
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M NOT GOING TO
COMMENT.
>> NONE OF US DESERVE THAT.
>> Jeff: SO, BRANDON, YOU HAVE
A VERY FAMOUS UNCLE IN THE
"SURVIVOR" WORLD, RUSSELL HANTZ,
WHO IS ONE OF THE MOST NOTORIOUS
PLAYERS EVER.
HAS ANYONE EVER ASKEDUE AND I
SAY THIS WITH RESPECT BUT IT
MIGHT NOT FEEL RESPECTFUL--
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> Jeff: IS IT IN THE BLOOD?
>> I'M STARTING TO COME TO THE
CONCLUSION THAT US HANTZS, WE
SPEAK OUR MINDS.
I'M PROUD OF THAT.
THAT'S SOMETHING I CAN WEAR
PROUDLY.
YOU ASK ME SOMETHING, I'M GOING
TO TELL YOU.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY ONE THING,
JEFF.
I NEVER HAD ANY BAD FEELINGS
TOWARDS BRANDON.
>> I DIDN'T, EITHER.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> WHERE THIS IS COMING FROM, I
HAVE NO IDEA.
YOUR WHOLE THING ABOUT ME BEING
IN CHARGE AND IN CONTROL IS JUST
A FIGMENT OF HIS IMAGINATION.
SO FOR HIM TO COME OUT HERE
RIGHT NOW AND SPEW WHAT HE
SPEWED, I HOPE YOU'RE STRONG
ENOUGH TO REALIZE JUST MAYBE YOU
MADE A MISTAKE.
>> SHUT UP.
>> THAT'S YOUR TYPICAL RESPONSE.
>> YOU NEED TO GROW UP.
>> YOU NEED TO SHUT UP.
GET A LITTLE BIT YOUNGER.
>> THAT'S THE WAY YOU TALK TO
YOUR ELDERS.
THAT'S RIGHT, YOU DO, DO THAT.
I REMEMBER WATCHING YOU TALKING
TO YOUR UNCLE WHO LET YOU LIVE
IN THE HOME.
YOU PROBABLY ARE TALKING TO YOUR
AUNT WHO--
>> YOU BRING MY FAMILY INTO
THIS.
I'M COME OVER HERE AND KNOCK
YOUR ( BLEEP ) HEAD OFF.
BRING MY KIDS INTO IN, BITCH.
>> Jeff: COME OVER.
FAVORITES, SO YOU WANT TO GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WHICH MEANS YOU WANT
TO FORFEIT THIS CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: AND SO, WHO'S GOT THE
IDOL?
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> Jeff: ERIK, WHY DON'T YOU
WALK IT OVER AND GIVE IT TO THE
FANS BECAUSE THEY WILL GLADLY
TAKE IT.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> Jeff: EASIEST IMMUNITY EVER
WON.
>> CAN YOU DO THE THING WITH
YOUR HANDS WHEN YOU SAY,
"IMMUNITY, THE FANS."
>> PLEASE JUST ONCE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GIVE IT TO YOU
ON YOUR WAY OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> Jeff: OKAY, WHY DON'T WE
JUST CUT TO THE CHASE.
WE'RE HAVING TRIBAL COUNCIL
RIGHT NOW
ALL RIGHT, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY GLI MEAN, THIS IS
TRIBAL.
ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A VOTE.
WITHOUT THE FIRE, WITHOUT THE
TORCHES
I'LL START WITH YOU, BRANDON.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO VOTE FOR.
>> PHILLIP!
>> Jeff: CORINNE, WHO ARE YOU
VOTING FOR?
BRANDON.
>> PHILLIP.
>> BRANDON.
>> BRENDA, BRANDON.
>> MALCOLM, BRANDON.
>> DAWN, BRANDON.
>> Jeff: ERR.
>>?
>> BRANDON.
>> LOVE YOU, BROTHER.
>> Jeff: ANDREA?
>> BRANDON.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GOOD
WITH THIS?
>> I'M GOOD WITH IT.
>> Jeff: SIXTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME, BRANDON HANTZ.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
I LOVE YOU.
BUT I KNOW YOU'RE FIRED UP.
>> YOU DON'T WANT ME GOING BACK.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE NOT GOING BACK
TO CAMP, NO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: THIS IS OVER.
ARE YOU GOOD WITH THAT?
>> I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHERE YOU'RE
GOING TO YOU WALK, STRAIGHT OUT
THIS WAY, AROUND THE BACK OF THE
CHALLENGE.
AND I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
COOL DOWN.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: AND I'LL COME FIND
YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, BROTHER THANKS,
MAN.
>> GUYS, IT WAS A PLEASURE.
>> GOOD LUCK, MAN.
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> KICK THEIR ASS.
PHILLIP, YOU'RE A BITCH!
>> Jeff: WELL, GAME JUST GOT A
LITTLE MORE INTERESTING.
IS THERE A SENSE OF RELIEF.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT WAS A LONG TIME COMING.
>> Jeff: DAWN, DO YOU THINK
THE TRIBE IS BETTER OFF?
>> I THINK BRANDON IS AND THAT'S
BEST FOR THE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO HERE'S
WHERE WE STAND.
FAVORITES NOW DOWN TO EIGHT
MEMBERS.
FANS AT SIX.
BIG MOMENTUM SHIFT POTENTIALLY
FOR YOU GUYS.
IT COMES IN AN ODD WAY, BUT
YOU'RE GOING HOME WITH IMMUNITY
AND YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
TAKE YOUR IDOL.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> BYE, GUYS!
>> I'LL TAKE IT.
>> I'LL TAKE TMAN.
>> A A WIN'S A WIN.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES, GRAB YOUR
STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": PHILLIP PLANS TO
TAKE OUT CORINNE.
>> CORINNE HAS GOT TO GO.
>> CORINNE PLANS TO TAKE OUT
PHILLIP.
>> PHILLIP IS THE MOST ANNOYING
PLAYER OUT HERE HANDS DOWN.
>> Jeff: NOBODY IS PLANNING ON
THIS BOTH TRIBES FEEL VERY GOOD
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD, BECAUSE IT'S ABOUT TO
CHANGE AGAIN.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> IT WAS NICE.
IT WAS GLORIOUS.
I SHOWED THEM THAT, HAY, THIS
GUY'S NOT GOING TO JUST KEEL
OVER AND DIE.
IF I'M GOING DOWN IN A BATTLE,
I'M GOING TO THROW ROCKS IN MY
ARMY.
I'M GOING TO GO OUT BRAVEHEART
STYLE.
I DON'T REGRET NONE OF IT
BECAUSE I PROVED MY POINT.
I WAS THE AUTHOR OF MY
ELIMINATION.