>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
DROP YOUR BUFFS, WE ARE
SWITCHING TRIBES.
AFTER A SURPRISE SWITCH, THE NEW
GOTA TRIBE HAD ALL THE MUSCLE
WHILE THE NEW BIKAL TRIBE --
>> I LIKE THIS PURPLE, GUYS.
>> Jeff: -- DIDN'T.
BUT ON BOTH TRIBES THE FAVORITES
OUTNUMBERED THE FANS 4-3.
AT GOTA, FANS TOOK TURNS
THROWING EACH OTHER UNDER THE
BUS.
>> SHERRI, IF YOU WANT TO VOTE
HER OUT, WE'RE WITH YOU.
>> REYNOLD.
HE'S THE BIGGEST SALESMAN.
>> Jeff: BUT AT BIKAL, THE
FANS WERE A HOT KPHAODTY.
PHILLIP WANT TO RECRUIT JULIA.
WHILE CORRINE WANTED MICHAEL.
>> IF I WASN'T A MORON I WOULD
TURN ON MY ENTIRE ALLIANCE TO
ALIGN WITH THE GAY.
THAT'S HOW MUCH I LIKE GAYS.
>> HELLO PHILIPPINES!
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE -- BIKAL APPEARS TO BE
ON SOME SORT OF MEDICATION
THEY'RE MOVING SO SLOW!
BIKAL FELL APART.
GOTA WINS IMMUNITY!
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL THE FANS KNEW
THEY WERE THE OBVIOUS TARGETS.
IS THERE A SENSE, MICHAEL, THAT
IS IT YOU, JULIA, OR MATT GOING
HOME TONIGHT?
>> 100%.
>> Jeff: IN THE END THEY WERE
RIGHT.
MATT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
13 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
LIKE, I REALLY --
>> DON'T BE SORRY.
>> IT CRUSHED ME TO HAVE TO LET
HIM GO.
I ADORED HIM.
>> LOVE MATT.
>> GREAT GUY.
BUT WE HAD TO MAKE A CHOICE AND
WE DECIDED TO KEEP YOU TWO.
>> THANK YOU TRIBAL COUNCIL
SUCKED.
MATT'S BEEN MY BOY SINCE DAY ONE
AND NOW I'M TOTALLY ON MY OWN.
YOU HONESTLY DON'T EVEN HAVE TO,
LIKE, REALLY EXPLAIN YOURSELVES.
I AM GOING TO CONTINUE TO TRY TO
BUILD TRUST WITH THESE GUYS AND
TRY TO BUILD FRIENDSHIPS AS WELL
SO THAT THEY WANT TO WORK WITH
ME AT THE MERGE.
I'M GREAT.
SERIOUSLY.
I'M HERE AND I'M --
>> I'M NOT LOOKING TO LOSE YOU,
SO --
>> I LIKE THAT.
I LIKE THAT WE CAN PLAY
TOGETHER.
>> I'M DEFINITELY WILLING TO
SACRIFICE ONE OF MY OWN TO KEEP
SOMEBODY ELSE AND I'M GOING TO
FIGHT TOOTH AND NAIL NOT TO HAVE
IT BE MICHAEL.
HE'S NOT GOING HOME ON MY WATCH.
I WOULD LIKE TO DUMP PHILLIP AS
SOON AS POSSIBLE.
THE PROBLEM IS YOU CAN'T MAKE
MOVES LIKE THAT THIS EARLY SO I
TRY REALLY HARD TO BE PATIENT
AND HOPE THAT THE TIME WILL COME
SOME TIME SOON.
YOU HAVE TO SURVIVE.
ONCE WE'RE AT THE MERGE WE'RE
KICKING ASS AND TAKING PEOPLE
NAMES.
WE'RE JUST TAKING PEOPLE OUT.
>> CORRINE CONSISTENTLY GOES AND
HAS CONVERSATIONS WITH PEOPLE
LIKE MICHAEL AND THEN DOESN'T
DISCLOSE TO US THE NATURE OF THE
CONVERSATIONS.
AND FOR ME, THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE.
>> I WANT HER GONE.
>> NOT NEXT, THOUGH.
>> MAYBE.
I DON'T WANT HER GOING TO THE
MERGE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE'S TOLD
HIM.
I WANT HER GONE.
>> SEE, HERE'S MY ONLY FEAR
ABOUT IT, STOCK?
WE DO THIS BEFORE THE MERGE, WE
MEET UP WITH OUR OLD TRIBE MATES
AND THEY'RE GOING TO THINK WHAT
THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
THEY WON'T WANT TO WORK WITH US
BECAUSE WE TURNED ON ONE OF OUR
CORE SIX.
>> I WANT CORRINE TO BE THE NEXT
PERSON GONE BUT IF I CAN NOT GET
RID OF CORRINE AND HER NEW GAY
FRIEND, AS SHE SAID, HE'LL BE
THE ONE THAT GOES HOME NEXT.
THIS IS ME AS A FEDERAL AGENT, I
DON'T TRUST THAT WOMAN.
>> OKAY.
TREEMAIL!
>> OH, BOY, HERE WE GO.
"THE STRONG MUST BEAR THE WEAK
IF YOU HOPE TO COMPETE.
THE TASTE OF VICTORY TODAY WILL
BE, OH, SO SWEET."
>> IT MENTIONS THE WEAK SO THERE
IS A PLACE FOR ME IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
THE TREEMAIL DID SAY THE STRONG
WILL CARRY THE WEEK.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF THE LATTER
CATEGORY SO IF THE SUCCESS OF
THIS CHALLENGE DEPENDS ON THE
EXISTENCE OF WEAK PEOPLE WE GOT
IT.
>> ANYTHING WITH STRENGTH IS A
LITTLE WORRISOME.
>> ANYTHING TO DO WITH THE UPPER
BODY, UPPER BACK SHOULDERS--
WITHOUT BEING ARROGANT-- I'M
ALMOST CERTAIN I CAN WIN IT.
>> TREEMAIL SAYS YOU HAVE TO BE
STRONG IN THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE ALL LOOKING AROUND LIKE,
"WELL, THAT SUCKS."
AND PHILLIP WITH HIS BRAVADO IS
"I GOT THIS, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M THE STRONGEST GUY OUT HERE."
OH, MY GOD.
>> I ONLY DO WHAT YOU CALL POWER
LIFTING.
I DON'T BLOW UP LIKE MUSCLE BODY
BUILDERS AND IT'S DECENTIVE
BECAUSE WHEN YOU GRAB SOMEONE
YOU CAN GENERALLY PULL THEM OR
HOLD THEM A LOT LONGER BUT YOU
DON'T LOOK LIKE YOU CAN.
THIS CHALLENGE HAS SOMETHING TO
DO WITH STRENGTH AND I THINK FOR
A LOT OF THEM THEY'RE CONCERNED
ABOUT IT.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT'S THE CASE
BUT I BELIEVE AS A PERSON AND A
MAN NOBODY IN THE OTHER TRIBE
CAN BEAT ME ARM WRESTLING.
I BEAT MOST MEN.
I LOVE TO FIND A SUCKER SOME GUY
WITH GREAT BIG MUSCLES WHO LOOKS
AT ME AND THINKS HE CAN BEAT ME.
SO PART OF MY TECHNIQUE WHEN I
GO IS TO GET THE GUY COME THAT
WAY.
THEN I TURN THAT WRIST LIKE THAT
DOWN LIKE THAT.
>> PHILLIP CHALLENGED ME TO AN
ARM WRESTLING MATCH.
HE NATURALLY WAS ABLE TO BEAT ME
QUICKLY.
>> PUT BOTH HANDS ON IT.
READY?
PUT MY HAND DOWN.
PUT ALL YOUR WEIGHT ON IT, MAN!
GET ON YOUR KNEES.
>> THEN TO UP THE ANTE AND TO
BUILD UP HIS EGO HE'LL DEMAND
THAT A BASICALLY PUT ALL MY
WEIGHT ON HIS ONE HAND.
(LAUGHS)
YOU'RE PROVING YOUR INCREDIBLE
STRENGTH.
I PUT A SIGNIFICANT PORTION OF
MY WEIGHT ON HIS FOREARM AND HE
MANAGED TO KEEP IT OFF THE
GROUND AND IF THE SMILE ON
PHILLIP'S FACE AFTER THAT, I
THINK HE FELT LIKE THE OLD
PHILLIP -- OR THE YOUNG PHILLIP.
>> I FEEL CONFIDENT.
I WAS FEELING CONFIDENT BUT I
FEEL MORE CONFIDENT.
IN CHANNELS MY ASSET IS MY WILL
OF AA LION AND MY DETERMINATION
OF A GORILLA.
I MAY BE OLD BUT I STILL HAVE
GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GOTA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW BIKAL TRIBE.
MATT VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
(APPLAUSE)
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'LL EACH BE WEARING A BELT
WHICH IS CLIPPED TO A ROPE SO
YOU WILL BE MOVING TOGETHER AS A
TRIBE.
IN ADDITION, YOU'LL EACH BE
CARRYING A 20-POUND SANDBAG.
STARTING ON OPPOSITE SIDES OF AN
OVAL COURSE YOU WILL RACE TO
CATCH THE OTHER TRIBE.
IF YOU GET TIRED, YOU CAN OPT
OUT AND GIVE YOUR WEIGHT TO
SOMEONE ELSE.
FIRST TRIBE TO CATCH THE OTHER
TRIBE WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: YOU'LL BE TAKEN TO A
NEARBY ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL
ENJOY A "SURVIVOR" STYLE COFFEE
BAR.
COOKIES.
>> COOKIES!
>> Jeff: CROISSANTS, BROWNIES.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: GO TARBGS YOU HAVE
ONE EXTRA PERSON.
GOING TO SIT SOMEBODY OUT?
>> BRENDA'S GOING TO SIT OUT.
>> Jeff: TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH OUT IN THE WATER.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> WHO WILL BE IN THE BACK?
>> WE HAVE MORE ENDURANCE AND
WE'RE STRONGER SO STAY EVEN FOR
THE FIRST LAP THEN WE'LL GAIN ON
THEM.
>> I'LL BE FIRST, HE'LL BE
SECOND.
I DON'T WANT TO BE IN THE BACK
BECAUSE IF I CAN RUN FASTER--
WHICH I THINK I CAN-- WITH MORE
WEIGHT I'M STUCK BEHIND YOU.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> IF SOMEONE DIES WE ALL HAVE
TO STOP.
>> ONE OF US WITH THE BAG.
>> BIKAL!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO.
FOR REWARDS, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> WE'RE GOOD.
RIGHT THERE IS GOOD.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO KEEP THAT
UP.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF ENDURANCE IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU ARE GOING TO GET EXHAUSTED.
>> WALK.
WALK.
>> HERE, COME A LITTLE FASTER.
>> THIS IS GOOD.
LET THEM THAT GAIN.
WE'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES BEING
VERY CAGEY, WALKING IT OFF RIGHT
NOW.
>> CAN'T WE JUST RUN?
>> Jeff: NOBODY RUNNING.
>> GUYS, THEY'RE CATCHING UP A
BIT.
>> READY?
HERE WE GO.
>> OH, LET'S JUST WALK IT.
THE GIRLS WILL TIRE.
>> Jeff: BIKAL PUTS THEIR
OLDEST GUY IN THE FRONT.
INTERESTING STRATEGIC MOVE.
GOTA PUTS ARGUABLY THEIR FITTEST
GUY IN THE FRONT ON A TRIBE OF
VERY FIT PEOPLE.
>> WE'RE ALREADY GAINING, GUYS,
GOOD JOB.
>> WHOO!
>> CAN WE RUN?
>> NOPE.
>> EVERY TIME YOU PASS BY THIS
MARK YOU CAN GET A SENSE OF
WHERE YOU ARE IN THIS CHALLENGE.
BIKAL IS QUICKLY BEHIND.
>> A LITTLE BIT MORE, GUYS, A
LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> A LITTLE SPEED BUT NOT A
SPRINT.
>> THEY'RE CATCHING US, GO A
LITTLE FASTER.
>> CAN WE RUN, PHILLIP?
>> I THINK YOU'LL TIRE MORE.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO GO,
20 YARDS.
COME ON.
>> Jeff: GOTA PICKING UP THE
PACE.
>> RUN!
>> RUN.
>> I CAN'T RUN, I'M TIRED.
I CAN'T RUN, GUYS.
>> Jeff: GOTA NOW ON THE SAME
SIDE OF THE COURSE AS BIKAL.
>> GUYS, THEY'RE SERIOUSLY
CATCHING UP.
>> THIS IS IT, WE CAN HUSTLE
RIGHT HERE.
READY, EVERYBODY?
ONE, TWO, THREE.
LET'S GO!
>> I CAN'T RUN, GUYS.
THE WEIGHT'S GOING TO COME TO ME
AND I WON'T BE ABLE TO DO
ANYTHING.
>> BUT THEY'RE GAINING ON US.
>> Jeff: GOTA SLOWLY BUT VERY
SURELY IS CATCHING BIKAL WHO HAS
YET TO DO ANYTHING BUT WALK.
THIS IS A STRATEGY, IT'S A
STRANGE ONE.
>> IT'S A STRANGE ONE!
>> A LITTLE MORE?
>> Jeff: GOTA GAINING ON BIKAL
LIKE A TIGER STALKING THEIR PREY
WAITING FOR THE MOMENT THE
POUNCE.
>> I CAN TASTE IT!
>> I NEED TO STEP OUT.
>> GIVE ME YOUR BAG.
>> Jeff: DAWN HAS OPTED OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE FOR BIKAL.
CORRINE CARRYING 40 POUNDS OF
SAND.
THIS IS NOT GOING WELL FOR
BIKAL.
>> GUYS, SAME THING, READY?
SPRINT, LET'S GO.
>> THEY'RE RUNNING AROUND THE
CURVE!
>> COME ON!
>> THEY'RE CATCHING US.
>> THEY'RE RUNNING AROUND THE
CURVE!
>> KEEP ON GOING SHERRI.
>> GUYS, THEY'RE COMING.
>> Jeff: BIKAL DOESN'T EVEN
SEEM CONCERNED.
>> LET'S GO!
>> YOU GUYS ARE AWESOME!
>> Jeff: GOTA CAN SENSE THE
KILL.
COCHRAN AND JULIA ARE OUT.
CORRINE WITH 60 POUNDS.
ANDREA GOES DOWN FOR GOTA.
>> RUN!
>> Jeff: PHILLIP FALLS DOWN!
THIS IS IT!
>> GO, GET HIM.
>> Jeff: IT'S OVER!
GOTA WINS REWARD!
>> THAT WAS THE WORST STRATEGY
EVER!
>> BRILLIANT STRATEGY.
PERFECT EXECUTION.
ALL DAY, EVERY TIME.
>> COOKIES AND BROWNIES!
COOKIES AND BROWNIES!
>> Jeff: GOTA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
NICE WIN.
NICE REWARD.
YOU'LL BE TAKEN TO ANOTHER
ISLAND, THE COFFEE BAR WILL BE
SET UP.
ENJOY THE AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> THEY'RE GOING TO GET SICK.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
THAT'S DIARRHEA FEST.
>> Jeff: BIKAL, GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> PHILLIP HAS JUST PUT HIMSELF
IN THIS ROLE THAT HE'S THE
LEADER AND HE'S JUST EXTREMELY
-- GOSH, ARROGANT SOUNDS SO MEAN
BUT THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
HE SEES ALL OF HIS STRENGTHS AND
NONE OF HIS WEAKNESSES.
WELCOME!
(SCREAMING)
>> OH, MY GOD!
MUFFIN!
MUFFIN?
>> .
>> CAN I HAVE A BROWNIE?
>> THAT'S PERFECT!
>> WINNING THE REWARD WAS A
GREAT WAY TO BOND WITH THE FANS
AND, YOU KNOW, THEY HAVEN'T WON
A REWARD YET.
CHEERS!
SO IT WAS NICE TO SEE THEM
ENJOYING A REWARD WITH US,
BONDING WITH THEM AS PEOPLE.
>> TO THE FIRST OF MANY REWARDS.
>> I WANT TO GET AS CLOSE TO
THEM AS POSSIBLE BEFORE, YOU
KNOW, I VOTE THEM OUT SO THEY
REMEMBER THE GOOD TIMES AND
STILL VOTE FOR ME IN THE END.
>> SPRING BREAK, NO PARENTS!
WHOO!
I JUST FEEL GREAT.
I MEAN, I'M A BACCAANALIAN, LIFE
IS MEANT TO INDULGE IN GLORIOUS
ABUNDANCE.
SO THIS REWARD IS RIGHT IN MY
SWEET SPOT.
NO PUN INTENDED.
(LAUGHS)
THIS ONE IS REALLY GOOD.
WINNING A REWARD LIKE THIS HELPS
TO SOLIDIFY BONDS BETWEEN PEOPLE
WITHIN A TRIBE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU!
>> AND I LOVE YOU.
>> AND ESPECIALLY MOST IMPORTANT
IS GETTING THESE BONDS GOING
WITH THE FAVORITES.
>> AND YOU.
MWAH.
CAFFEINE IS STARTING TO KICK IN!
>> CAN'T TELL.
>> WITH NEW GOTA EVERYONE ON THE
SURFACE IS JUST SMILING.
ALL WE DO IS WIN CHALLENGES AND
PARTY.
IT'S JUST ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY,
REALLY.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME THERE'S A
GAME GOING ON AND WHEN IT COMES
DOWN TO IT I KNOW I'M GOING TO
BE IN TROUBLE WHEN IT COMES
MERGE TIME NO ONE WANTS TO GO TO
THE END WITH ME.
NOT THAT I BLAME THEM BUT I HAVE
TO MAKE MY MOVE SOON.
I'M KEEPING A SMILE BUT GETTING
MY PIECES READY TO TAKE CONTROL
OF THIS GAME.
>> SAEURBG ASLEEP WITH A SMILE
AND A COOKIE IN HIS HAND.
JUST HAPPY TO KNOW THAT IT'S
THERE.
(LAUGHTER)
>> ONCE THEY LINED UP IT WAS
CLEAR THEIR LEGS WERE GOING TO
OUTWALK US OR OUTRUN US.
JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
AND THEY HAD YOUTH SO THEY HAD
EVERY COMPONENT THEY NEEDED TO
WIN THAT CHALLENGE.
>> WE JUST LOST OUR REWARD
CHALLENGE AND I'M GOING TO BLAME
THE WHOLE THING ON PHILLIP AND
PHILLIP CAN TAKE THE FALL FOR
THIS.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO GO TO TRIBAL
TONIGHT SO -- WHAT?
>> OH, THIS IS A REWARD
CHALLENGE.
>> NO DOWN.
NO DOWN.
>> YOU TUB BILUNCHBOX!
I HAVE YET TO SEE AN AB ON YOU.
I DON'T SEE ANY PECTORAL
MUSCLES.
HE'S AN AMOEBA.
HE'S A LOOSE PEN POUNDS OF
POTATOES IN A FIVE-POUND SACK.
HE'S JUST A MESS.
BUT EVERYONE ELSE SEES HIS TRUE
COLORS AND HE BLOWS THE NEXT
CHALLENGE FOR US MAYBE WE TAKE
HIM OUT.
I COULD HAVE TAKEN EVERYBODY'S
WEIGHTS AND DONE THE ENTIRE
THING MYSELF AND WON IT.
HE'S THE WORST.
>> HE HAS THIS INFLATED SENSE OF
I'M THE STRONGEST MAN IN THE
WORLD, I'M MR. UNIVERSE
STKWHR-FPLT IT'S SO FRUSTRATING.
I DON'T WANT TO KEEP PLAYING
THIS GAME WITH HIM.
>> YEAH.
PHILLIP AND CORRINE HATE EACH
OTHER.
THERE'S SO MUCH FRACTURE AND
DIVISION WITHIN THE FAVORITES ON
THIS TRIPE IT'S LIKE A DEATH
SENTENCE.
SOMETHING IS GOING TO HAPPEN AT
ONE POINT OR ANOTHER.
>> IT'S A JOKE.
>> I'M GOING TO BE PUSHING THAT
WE CERTAINLY VOTE OFF A FAN
WHICH IS NOT EVEN A CERTAINTY
BECAUSE MICHAEL HAS GOTTEN VERY,
VERY CLOSE WITH CORRINE.
>> IF YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS OF HOW
WE CAN REEL HIM IN, PLEASE LET
ME KNOW.
>> JULIA, ON THE OTHER HAND, IS
SUCH A NONENTITY OUT HERE.
I'M TEMPTED TO SAY SHE HAS A
VANILLA PERSONALITY BUT I FEEL
LIKE THAT WOULD BE DOING A GREAT
DISSERVICE TO THE FLAVOR
VANILLA.
PEOPLE ACTIVELY SEEK OUT
VANILLA-FLAVORED PRODUCTS.
CHILDREN CLAMOR TO GET VANILLA
ICE CREAM CONE.
NOBODY IS CLAMORING FOR ANYTHING
JULIA-FLAVORED.
EXCEPT FOR PHILLIP.
PHILLIP HAS GROWN VERY, VERY
CLOSE TO JULIA.
AND I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE WHY.
>> IF YOU WERE TO SURVIVE AND
MAKE IT TO THE MERGE I'D WANT
YOU TO BE FRIEND WITH YOUR OTHER
TRIBE MATES, LEARN WHAT YOU
LEARN AND DON'T GO BACK.
MIGHT AS WELL BE A PART OF THE
WINNING STRATEGY AND SAY, HEY,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I MADE A BIG MOVE.
THE PROBLEM WITH BEING A DOUBLE
AGENT IS-- BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
EFFECTIVELY YOU BECOME-- I'D
LIKE TO MAKE YOU ONE OF THE
BEST.
>> UNDERSTOOD.
>> DON'T SHARE IT WITH ANYONE
ELSE, INCLUDING ANY MEMBER OF
OUR TRIBE.
I THINK I'VE DONE A VERY GOOD
JOB WITH JULIA AND I THINK I'VE
GOT MY FIRST DOUBLE AGENT.
I SHARE WITH HER SOME
INFORMATION AND I TOLD HER DON'T
SHARE IT WITH ANYONE ELSE.
IF SHE FEELS SHE'S IN TROUBLE
SHE CAN LET ME KNOW AND I'LL DO
EVERYTHING IN MY POWER TO MAKE
SURE SHE STAYS IN THE GAME.
I CAN'T SAY EXACTLY WHERE YOU
WOULD END.
>> YEAH?
>> BUT YOU COULD GO FAR.
>> WHAT'S INTERESTING WITH FILL
SLIP THAT I DON'T FIND HIM TO BE
AN INTIMIDATING CHARACTER AT
ALL.
BUT WHEN HE'S LIKELY TELL YOU TO
DO THIS AND YOU WILL DO IT.
I UNDERSTAND THAT AT THIS POINT
IF I HAVE ANY HOPE OF STAYING IN
THE GAME THAT'S WHAT I HAVE TO
DO.
>> FULLY UNDERSTOOD.
BUT IT COMES A POINT WHEN HE'S
GOING TO REALLY DESTRUCT THE
UNITY OF THE TRIBE BY DRIVING
EVERYONE CRAZY SO WHY NOT GET
RID OF HIM?
>> SO WE HAVE SEVEN HERE, THEY
HAVE SIX.
>> THEY HAVE SIX.
IMMUNITY TOMORROW.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> WHEN PEOPLE HAVE THE SAME
PROBLEM, IT'S EASY TO BRING THEM
TOGETHER.
AND THE FOUR ALPHA MALES IN THIS
GAME-- BEING MYSELF, REYNOLD,
EDDIE AND ERIC-- ARE GOING TO
HAVE A BIG PROBLEM COME MERGE
TIME.
THE ATHLETIC GUYS ARE GOING TO
GET TARGETED AND KNOCKED OUT OF
THE GAME.
WHAT I NEED TO DO IS SPEARHEAD
HAVING THESE FOUR GUYS JOIN
FORCES.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO STICK
TOGETHER GOING INTO THE MERGE.
THE FOUR OF US, THE GUYS, ARE
GOING TO BE THE FIRST FOUR
TARGETS.
WE KNOW THAT.
IT'S GOT TO BE THE FOUR GUYS.
I'LL BRING IN ERIC AND YOU HAVE
TO BRING IN EDDIE.
>> EDDIE AND ARE 100% FULL
DISCLOSURE EACH-TO-EACH OTHER
TIGHT HONEST.
AND I AM FULLY ON THE PAGE WITH
THAT.
UP TO THIS POINT, I'VE BEEN LIED
TO A LOT BY MY PREVIOUS TRIBE SO
AT THIS POINT THE ONLY PERSON I
BELIEVE IS EDDIE.
I BELIEVE YOU.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE NO REASON TO BE
TALKING TO ME RIGHT NOW.
>> WE'RE IN THE SAME BOAT.
>> IN A GAME WHERE YOU CAN NOT
TRUST ANYBODY IT'S HARD TO TELL.
YOU STILL HAVE TO KIND OF RELY
ON YOUR INSTINCTS.
>> WE'RE THE SAME CHARACTER.
>> THE EXACT SAME PERSON.
>> AND MALCOLM JUST STRIKES ME
AS THE TYPE OF GUY THAT IS LIKE
ME AND HE SEES THAT I CAN HELP
HIM AND HE CAN DEFINITELY HELP
ME.
SO THIS ONE FEELS RIGHT AND THIS
WILL BE THE ONE THAT IS THE NAIL
IN THE COFFIN FOR ME IF I'M
WRONG.
WOULD THEY TELL YOU IF THEY WERE
GOING FOR ME?
>> YEAH, BECAUSE THEY THINK I'M
ON BOARD AND IF IT IS, LIKE,
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
>> WILL YOU TELL ME?
>> YEAH, I WILL.
IF YOU CAN PROTECT YOURSELF I'LL
TELL YOU.
>> I HAVE THE IDOL.
>> I WILL DEFINITELY TELL YOU.
>> DON'T MENTION ABOUT THE IDOL.
>> ALL RIGHT, SICK.
>> IF I DIDN'T COMPLETELY TRUST
REYNOLD AFTER SELLING HIM ON
THIS IDEA, I TRUST HIM NOW
BECAUSE HE'S GONE SO OVER THE
TOP UNNECESSARILY TO PROVE HIS
LOYAL THEY HE'S TOLD ME ABOUT
HIS IDOL.
I'VE HAD AN IDOL SINCE DAY FOUR.
I WOULDN'T OFFER TO DO THAT FOR
SOME STRANGER WHO JUST CAME TO
ME SO WITH THIS INFORMATION I'M
THE ONLY ONE IN THE GAME WHO
KNOWS WHERE BOTH IDOLS ARE AND I
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE LOOK ON
SOME PEOPLE'S FACES WHEN I TAKE
CONTROL OF THIS GAME.
GOD, I CAN'T WAIT!
(LAUGHS)
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING NEXT STAGE IN THE GAME.
>> OBVIOUSLY WHATEVER YOUR
DYNAMIC IS WITH PHIL THAT'S YOUR
BUSINESS.
THE THING IS THAT I TALKED WITH
PHIL AND HE GAVE ME THE SENSE
THAT MAYBE HE WOULD WANT TO TAKE
ME ALONG FOR NEIGHBOR A NEW
ALLIANCE HE WANTS TO DO AFTER
THE MERGE.
SO PART OF ME FELT A LITTLE
INDEBTED TO HIM BUT I FEEL LIKE
I'M BEING BULLIED.
>> I THINK HE'S TRYING TO BRING
YOU IN.
>> LIKE HE'S PLAYING HIS GAME --
>> FOR HIM.
>> AT THIS POINT IT'S WORKING
FOR ME, TOO.
>> JULIA APPROACHED ME AND JUST
SAID "PHILLIP REALLY WANTS ME TO
WORK WITH HIM.
I'M OKAY WORKING UNDER HIM IF
THAT KEEPS ME IN THE GAME."
>> WHAT IF EVERYONE JUST
OVERTHREW PHIL.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT'S WHAT I
WANT TO DO BUT WHAT'S STOPPING
PEOPLE?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE DYNAMIC
IS.
BASED ON THE TIME I'VE SPENT
WITH JULIA SHE WASN'T SEEMS VERY
AWARE OF THE GAME SO IT'S
HELPFUL TO KNOW SHE'S THINKING
MORE THAN WE THOUGHT SHE WAS.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, I'M NOT GOING
TO SAY A SINGLE THING TO
ANYBODY.
>> OH, OH, OH!
JULIA APPROACHED ME AND SHE'S
LIKE HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT ME IF
I WORK WITH PHILLIP IT FEELS
LIKE THAT WOULD BE A GOOD THING
FOR ME LONG TERM.
>> SHE'S AN IDIOT.
I SPECIFICALLY TOLD HER NOT TO
SAY THAT TO ANYONE.
>> THAT'S WHY I TOLD YOU.
>> WHAT AN IDIOT.
JULIA, ORIGINALLY I WANTED HER
HERE.
I DID.
BUT SHE'S MANAGED TO COMMIT
SEVERAL FAUX PAS IN TERMS OF
"SURVIVOR" PLAY.
>> SHE NEEDS TO GO.
>> OH, YEAH, I'VE ALREADY
CONCLUDED THAT.
I GAVE HER A PIECE OF
INFORMATION AND I SAID "YOU'RE
NOT GO-TO-GO TO ANYONE ELSE FOR
VALIDATION."
OF COURSE SHE WENT TO DAWN AND
DAWN, OF COURSE, CAME TO ME AND
TOLD ME THAT AND JULIA WON'T
KNOW UNTIL SHE'S WALKING DOWN
THAT AISLE WITH HER TORCH OUT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
ANDREA, I WILL TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, THREE
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL
PADDLE OUT INTO THE OCEAN.
YOU'LL DIVE DOWN AND RELEASE A
STATUE.
YOU'LL THEN BRING IT BACK TO
SHORE AND PLACE IT AT THE BASE
OF A TOWER.
THEN THREE OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL USE A GRAPPLING HOOK TO
RETRIEVE KEYS.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL FIVE
KEYS YOU'LL UNLOCK THE TOWER AND
PULL YOUR STATUE TO THE TOP.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
GOTA, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON.
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE THIS TIME?
>> SHERRI.
>> Jeff: SHERRI, TAKE A SPOT
ON THE BENCH.
>> BYE, SHERRI.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO!
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS DAWN, CORRINE AND MICHAEL
FOR BIKAL, IT IS BRENDA, EDDIE
AND ERIC FOR GOTA.
THEY'RE OFF TO A QUICK START.
PERFECT, GUYS!
BIKAL JUST ABOUT GOES OVER.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A LOT OF TEAM
WORK TO STAY ON COURSE.
>> ROW!
>> Jeff: GOTA ONCE AGAIN IN A
CHALLENGE OFF TO A FAST START
AND AN EARLY LEAD.
YOU'VE GOT TO CLIP IN FIRST!
>> ERIC, OTHER SIDE!
>> Jeff: GOTA NOW OFF COURSE.
BIKAL NOW MAKING GOOD WORK OF
THAT.
DAWN AND MICHAEL DOING A NICE
JOB OF GETTING BIKAL BACK INTO
THIS.
BIKAL NOW IS IN THE LEAD!
NOW BOTH TRIBES ARE FLIPPING IN.
>> ATTA GIRL, GREEN!
>> Jeff: GOTA'S CLIPPED IN.
BIKAL IS CLIPPED IN.
GET IN THE WATER!
>> Jeff: GOTA VERY QUICKLY HAS
THEIR STATUE TO THE TOP.
BIKAL HAS THEIR STATUE TO THE
WATER.
>> COME ON, GUYS, YOU GOT IT!
LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: THAT STATUE IS VERY
HEAVY.
IT WILL TAKE ALL THREE PEOPLE
WORKING TOGETHER.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: GOTA HAS THEIR STATUE
IN THE BOAT.
BIKAL HAS THEIR STATUE IN THE
BOAT.
GOTA IS UNCLIPPED AND HEADING
BACK.
NOW BIKAL HAS IT RELEASED AND
THEY'RE ABOUT TO TIP.
>> OH, OH!
LEAN!
>> Jeff: ANOTHER RECOVERY BY
BIKAL.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS!
>> YOU GOT IT!
>> Jeff: BIKAL NOW BACK ON
TRACK.
>> ROW!
ROW!
>> Jeff: GOTA GETS IT
TOGETHER.
TEARING TO SHORE.
YOU'VE GOT TO CLIP IN!
>> GOT IT?
>> CLIPPED IN.
>> Jeff: GOTA'S TO SHORE,
THEY'RE CLIPPED IN.
BIKAL IS BACK TO SHORE.
GOTA NOW CAN START GOING FOR
THEIR KEYS.
BIKAL HAS GOT TO GET THEIR
STATUE IN THE TOWER.
>> TURN IT!
TURN IT!
>> Jeff: BIKAL HAS THEIR
STATUE IN THE TOWER.
THEY CAN START TOSSING.
IT IS REYNOLD USING THE
GRAPPLING HOOK FOR GOTA.
PHILLIP TOSSING THAT ROPE FOR
BIKAL.
>> THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD WITH A NICE
TOSS.
REYNOLD SECURE IT IS FIRST KEY
FOR GOTA.
PHILLIP JUST MISSES FOR BIKAL.
REYNOLD WITH ANOTHER NICE TOSS,
CAN HE HOOK ANOTHER ONE?
HE'S GOT I.
>> THAT'S IT, REYNOLD.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP WITH A NICE
TOSS.
CAN HE HOOK IT?
JUST MISSES.
REYNOLD WITH ANOTHER GREAT TOSS!
AND THE THIRD KEY.
>> THAT'S A NICE TOSS, PHILLIP.
>> Jeff: THIS COULD DO IT FOR
PHILLIP.
IT'S RIGHT ON.
PHILLIP WITH THE FIRST RING FOR
BIKAL.
REYNOLD WITH THE FOURTH KEY FOR
GOTA.
REYNOLD ON FIRE!
>> THAT'S A NICE TOSS, PHILIP.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP WITH A NICE
TOSS.
PHILLIP HAS THE SECOND KEY FOR
BIKAL.
REYNOLD WITH A NICE TOSS.
THIS COULD DO IT, IT WOULD BE
THE FIFTH KEY FOR GOTA.
JUST MISSES.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
BIG LEAD.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP WITH ANOTHER
NICE TOSS.
HE'S GOT TO MAKE THAT WORK.
HE'S GOT IT!
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: BIKAL IS CATCHING UP.
IT'S A HUGE COMEBACK RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: REYNOLD WITH THE
FIFTH KEY RIGHT IN SIGHT.
THIS COULD DO IT FOR GOTA.
PHILLIP STILL LOOKING FOR TWO
FINAL KEYS.
HE'S RIGHT ON IT.
CAN HE MAKE IT WORK?
JUST MISSES.
REYNOLD HAS THAT FIFTH KEY.
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: BIKAL NEEDS TO GET
MOVING.
REYNOLD AND ANDREA GOING TO TRY
TO OPEN THAT LOCK FOR GO.
A PHILLIP AGAIN JUST MISSES.
ANDREA HAS IT FOR GOTA.
ALL THEY HAVE TO DO NOW IS PULL
THAT ROPE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
>> Jeff: THIS WILL DO IT.
GOTA WINS IMMUNITY!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
GOTA, CONGRATULATIONS AGAIN!
(APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT, GOTA, ENJOY THE NIGHT
OFF.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
BIKAL, AFTER 19 DAYS, ONE OF YOU
WILL BE THE EIGHTH PERSON TO
LEAVE THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE THE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> THOSE THINGS WOULD BE A LOT
OF FUN IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE SO
MUCH RIDING ON THEM.
>> YEAH, THEY WOULD.
>> THE GRAPPLING IS HARDER THAN
IT LOOKS.
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHEN WE GOT BACK TO CAMP
SPIRITS WERE UNDERSTANDABLY A
LITTLE BIT LOW.
WE JUST LOST.
AND PHILLIP WAS SULKING AROUND
EYEING OUT EVERYBODY AND THEN HE
QUICKLY AND COVERTLY PULLED ME
ASIDE AND WHISPERED INTENSELY --
>> I HAVE A CONFESSION.
>> AND MY MIND STARTS RACING
INSTANTLY.
HAS HE DONE SOMETHING AROUND
CAMP.
IS HE GOING TO BETRAY CORRINE
TONIGHT?
WHAT COULD IT POSSIBLY BE?
>> I LOVE WHAT JEFF HAD IN STORE
FOR US TODAY FOR THE CHALLENGE.
IT WAS AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
WE WERE CLOSE IN THE CHALLENGE,
PROBABLY COULD HAVE WON THAT
CHALLENGE-- HAD I WANTED TO.
I DIDN'T WANT TO WIN THAT
CHALLENGE.
>> (LAUGHS)
I KNEW YOU WERE GOING SAY THAT.
>> OKAY?
I COULDN'T SEE JULIE AT THE
MERGE.
>> IT ALL MAKES SENSE!
WE HAD TO THROW THE CHALLENGE IN
ORDER TO GET RID OF ONE OF THESE
FANS OR ELSE WE WERE DOOMED.
AND THAT'S THE ONLY REASON WHY
PHILLIP WAS UNABLE TO
SUCCESSFULLY THROW A GRAPPLING
HOOK.
I MEAN, IT'S COMPLETE CRAP.
>> IT HIT ME ONCE I SAW IT WAS A
GRAPPLING HOOK, I'LL MAKE A
GALLANT EFFORT BUT IT WON'T BE
WHERE IT NEEDS TO BE BECAUSE I
WOULD HAVE TOSSED IT SLIGHTLY
DIFFERENTLY.
>> YOU CAN'T MAKE UP THIS LEVEL
OF DELUSION AND THAT'S WHAT
EXCITES ME ABOUT PLAYING WITH
PHILLIP.
I THINK HE'S CONVINCED HE THREW
THE CHALLENGE.
SOME OF THE RAZZLE DAZZLE.
>> SLOWING IT DOWN, PULLING IT
BACK.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN HUSTLING TO
GET IT BACK.
>> HE WASN'T THROWING THE
CHALLENGE, HE WAS TRYING HIS
HARDEST, HE WAS IN FULL SPY
MODE.
CAN YOU IMAGINE THE SPEECH HE
WOULD HAVE GIVEN AT CAMP HAD HE
SUCCESSFULLY THROWN A GRAPPLING
HOOK, THE SPY'S BASIC TOOL, AT A
CHALLENGE AND WON THE CHALLENGE
FOR US?
IT'S JUST -- (LAUGHS)
IT'S ABSURD!
>> WHEN A LION, THE MALE LION
WITH HIS MANE WHEN HE COMESES
ACROSS ANOTHER PRIDE OF LIONS OF
FEMALES AND THERE'S CUBS AND THE
MALE ISN'T AROUND, WHAT DOES HE
DO?
HE KILLS ALL THE CUBS.
>> (LAUGHS)
>> YOU KNOW WHY?
THOSE ARE POTENTIAL RIVALS.
SO TODAY --
>> TAKING OUT THE CUBS.
>> WE'RE STILL ON BOARD WITH
SLITTING, RIGHT?
>> WE'RE GOING TO SPLIT BECAUSE
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T
HAVE THE IDOL.
>> THE NUMBERS ARE FOUR
FAVORITES AND TWO FANS.
THAT NUMBERS ADVANTAGE MEANS
THAT THE FOUR OF US CAN SPLIT
OUR VOTES ACROSS THE TWO
REMAINING FANS, FLUSH OUT ANY
POSSIBLE IDOLS AND AND WE CAN
GET RID OF JULIA.
>I STILL THINK
WE SHOULD SPLIT THE VOTES.
>> I'M NOT SPLITTING.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD.
>> THERE'S NO REASON.
>> IT'S COMMON SENSE.
WHY NOT?
IF WE HAVE THE NUMBERS WHY NOT
DO IT.
>> WHY ARE YOU WORRIED?
>> BECAUSE AS SOON AS WE MERGE I
WANT MIKE TO WORK WITH US LONG
TERM SO I WANT TO DO EVERYTHING
IN MY POWER TO MAKE SURE HE
FEELS SAFE, COMFORTABLE, AND
TRUSTS US.
I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA OF
SPLITTING VOTES BECAUSE TO ME I
KNOW I WANT TO SEND JULIA HOME,
I KNOW THERE'S NO IDOL BECAUSE I
HAVE THE IDOL WITH MALCOLM AND I
DON'T WANT TO GO INTO A MERGE
HAVING MICHAEL SECOND GUESSING
WHAT'S GOING ON.
IT'S BAD BUSINESS.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY I CAN'T
CONVINCE THE REST OF THE
ALLIANCE OF THAT.
>> I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT HOW HE
FEELS ABOUT IT.
I HAVE THE NUMBERS WITHOUT HIM.
I DON'T NEED HIM.
>> SHH!
>> I'M JUST SAYING I DON'T NEED
HIM SO WHY SHOULD BY EXTRA --
>> WE DO NEED HIM.
>> YOU DON'T NEED HIM.
>> YOU MIGHT.
>> WE MIGHT BUT WE MIGHT NOT.
I'M NOT GOING TO PUT THEM ALL IN
ONE BASKET.
THAT'S THE WAY I PLAY THE GAME.
>> I GET IT.
DON'T WALK AWAY.
>> I PLAYED WITH BOSTON ROB.
>> OKAY, PHILLIP, THAT'S FINE.
DON'T YELL AT ME.
>> I'M NOT YELLING AT YOU!
>> YOU ARE.
>> NO, I'M NOT SAYING WHAT YOU
WANT ME TO HEAR.
>> CORRINE, WHO'S IN LOVE WITH
MICHAEL, SEEMS TO HAVE THIS
NOTION THAT OH, NO, NO, NO, IT
HAS TO BE A SHOW OF UNITY.
JUST A MOMENT HIM THINKING THAT
WE ARE NOT 100% BEHIND HIM.
I'M NOT AN IDIOT.
I DO SEE IT AND I SEE HER
PUTTING HER SELFISH INTERESTS
ABOVE THE FAVORITES.
THE FOUR ALLIANCE THAT'S ON THE
BEACH RIGHT NOW IS THE THREE OF
US, NOT CORRINE.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE BULLIED IN
DOING SOMETHING I AT MY CORE
SAYS YOU DON'T DO TO SATISFY HER
NEW FRIEND.
I PLAYED WITH THE SMARTEST
PLAYER THAT I'VE EVER HAD AN
OPPORTUNITY TO PLAY WITH, BOSTON
ROB.
AND I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT B.R.
WOULD DO IN THIS SITUATION.
WHAT B.R. WOULD DO IS SAY OKAY,
CORRINE, WE VOTE MICHAEL OUT THE
GAME.
I'M GOING TO CAST MY VOTE ON
MICHAEL.
HE'S SMART, HE'S CLEVER, HE'S
DOING IT BY THE BOOK, EXACTLY
WHAT HE'S SUPPOSED TO DO TO STAY
IN THE GAME.
>> WHAT'D WE DECIDE.
>> YOU MADE IT CLEAR FROM THE
GET-GO WHO YOUR CHOICE WAS.
I TOOK ALL EMOTION OUT OF IT.
>> PHILLIP --
>> I'M EXPLAINING --
>> YOU'RE NOT LETTING ME TALK AT
ALL.
>> BECAUSE YOU WALKED UP ON A
CONVERSATION I WAS HAVING WITH
THE THREE OF THEM.
>> WE'RE IN AN ALLIANCE,
PHILLIP.
>> SO WHAT?
>> I DON'T INTERRUPT YOU WHEN
YOU HAVE A MEETING.
WHEN YOU WALK OVER WITH DAWN DO
I WALK OVER AND GO BLAH?
I DON'T.
I LET YOU FINISH YOUR
CONVERSATION.
>> YOU'RE BEING SO MEAN TO ME
PHILLIP.
>> I'M NOT BEING MEAN.
>> YES, YOU ARE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU'RE FEELING THAT WAY LET
ME CONTINUE WITH THE
CONVERSATION I WAS HAVING WITH
ME, THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> PHILLIP IS BEYOND AWFUL.
LIKE, IF THIS WAS THE REAL WORLD
I WOULD KICK HIS ASS BUT FOR ME
IT'S A WAITING GAME UNTIL I GET
TO HOLD UP THAT PARCHMENT AND GO
THIS IS WHAT BOSTON ROB WOULD
HAVE DONE.
>> LIKE, I'M NOT STUPID.
>> OKAY.
>> I AM VERY, VERY CONCERNED
ABOUT HER RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM.
SHE WAS NEVER PART OF THE CORE
ALLIANCE.
>> AGREED.
>> I SENSE HER LOVE FOR HIM IS
GREATER THAN IT IS FOR ME.
>> RIGHT.
>> THAT'S A PROBLEM.
>> RIGHT, AGREED.
>> PHILLIP WANTS TO VOTE OFF
MICHAEL.
I DON'T KNOW IF THIS IS THE PLAN
SET IN STONE BUT IT'S CLEARLY
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH JULIA OR
MICHAEL.
IT'S MASKING SOMETHING THAT'S
ABOUT TO COME TO THE SURFACE AND
TONIGHT'S VOTE WILL PROBABLY BE
WHAT SETS INTO MOTION A SERIES
OF EVENTS THAT COMPLETELY BRING
THIS PHILLIP/CORRINE FEUD TO THE
SURFACE AND MAKE IT CLEAR WHY
THEY CAN'T PLAY TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: SO MICHAEL, 19 DAYS
IN, THIS TRIBE IN A STATE OF
DESPAIR.
IS IT HARD TO KEEP MORALE UP?
>> OF COURSE, YEAH.
I MEAN MAYBE IT BRINGS OUT A
LITTLE BIT OF TENSION IN THE
TRIBE WHEN MORALE IS LOW.
>> Jeff: YA JULIA, IF IT'S
STILL FANS VERSUS FAVORITES YOU
WOULD HAVE A REASON TO BE TENSE.
WHY WOULD ANYONE ELSE BE TENSE?
>> YOU KNOW, THE FAVORITES DO
HAVE THE NUMBERS AND SO I KNOW
THEY'RE THINKING WAY PAST THIS
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THEY HAVE THEIR GAMES AND THEIR
ALLIANCES SO I TOTALLY SEE HOW
THEY WOULD BE TENSE AS WELL.
>> Jeff: CORRINE, NOW I'M
CONNECTING THE DOTS.
IS THE TENSION WITHIN THE FOUR
FAVORITES COMING DOWN TO "DO WE
KEEP MICHAEL OR DO WE KEEP
JULIA"?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
GOING INTO A POSSIBLE MERGE IS A
REALLY SERIOUS THING AND YOU
DON'T WANT TO SCREWING IN UP
HERE AND THEN REGRET IT DOWN THE
LINE.
>> I WANTED TO ADD, JEFF, IT'S
ABOUT UNDERSTANDING THE PROCESS.
SOMETIMES FOR CORRINE AND MYSELF
WE MIGHT CLASH ON A POINT.
WE'RE ACTUALLY TALKING ABOUT THE
SAME THING BUT THE PROCESS ON
HOW WE GO ABOUT GETTING THERE IS
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
>> Jeff: DAWN, HAVE YOU SEEN
PHILLIP AND CORRINE AS THEY TRY
TO WORK THROUGH A DECISION?
>> SEEN IT, FELT IT.
(LAUGHS)
BEEN MANY BETWEEN IT.
YEAH.
BUT I THINK AN ALLIANCE LIKE
THIS IS KIND OF ORGANIC, IN A
WAY.
I'VE LEARNED THAT IF WE ALL HAVE
THE SAME GOAL AT THE END THE
CONFLICT MAY BE OKAY IF WE STAY
COMMITTED.
>> Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT
TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
GREAT JOB ON THE FIRST HALF,
FELL APART ON THE SECOND HALF.
PHILLIP, YOU PUT YOURSELF IN
THAT HERO ROLE AGAIN.
>> NO, I DON'T SEE IT THAT WAY.
I SEE IT AS PUTTING MYSELF IN
THE ROLE THAT EVERYONE HAD
PREVIOUSLY SEEN ON THREE OTHER
OCCASIONS WHERE I PREVAILED.
>> Jeff: WHO LOST THIS
CHALLENGE TODAY?
>> I WOULD SAY I LOST THE
PORTION.
>> Jeff: THAT'S WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
THE GUY WHO SAYS "GIMME THE
BALL" IS THE GUY SAYING "COUNT
ON ME.
".
>> BUT I'M ALSO THE GUY WHO WHEN
THE STATUE CAME UP OUT OF THE
BOAT I PICKED IT UP BY MYSELF
WHERE THE OTHER TEAM TOOK THREE
MEN TO CARRY IT.
MAYBE THAT TIRED ME OUT, I DON'T
KNOW.
ALL YOU CAN DO IS MAKE SURE THE
NEXT DAY YOU PUT FORTH ANOTHER
110%, THAT'S HOW WINNERS BECOME
WINNERS.
>> Jeff: SO MICHAEL, YOU LOSE
ANOTHER IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, HERE
WE ARE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT'S YOU OR JULIA.
HOW DO YOU PITCH YOURSELF TO
THESE FOUR ABOUT WHY THEY SHOULD
KEEP YOU?
>> WELL, I DIDN'T START TODAY, I
STARTED WHEN I LANDED ON THE
BEACH.
AND I HAVEN'T STOPPED.
I'VE JUST BEEN WORKING HARD
TRYING TO GET EVERYBODY TO TRUST
ME SO THAT THEY CAN KNOW THAT
WHEN IT COMES TO THE MERGE THEY
FEEL COMFORTABLE MOVING FORWARD
WITH ME.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, CORRINE WAS
VERY VOCAL LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL
ABOUT SAYING "I LIKE TO PLAY
WITH THE GAYS."
SO COULD MICHAEL'S FRIENDSHIP
WITH CORRINE WORK AGAINST HIM?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, IF PEOPLE
PERCEIVE MICHAEL AS BEING MORE
CONNECTED TO CORRINE AND MORE
LIKELY TO WANT TO WORK SOLELY
WITH HER, I CAN SEE THAT WORKING
AGAINST HIM.
>> LOOK, THIS IS A LITTLE
GROSSLY EXAGGERATED.
LIKE, I'VE ONLY KNOWN HIM FOR A
HANDFUL OF DAYS AND I THINK IT'S
NEAT THAT HE'S GAY.
BUT A TWOSOME ALLIANCE THIS DOES
NOT MAKE, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>>
>> Jeff: SO MICHAEL, WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN?
>> I WANT TO GET TO THE VOTE.
I WANTED TO GET TO THE VOTE AS
SOON AS WE GOT BACK FROM THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE, YOU KNOW, A
CAT HANGING ON TO A TREE FOR,
LIKE, FOUR OR FIVE DAYS GOING
LIKE OH, MY GOD, WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN?
YOU KNOW?
AND I'M READY TO FIND OUT.
>> Jeff: JULIA, HOW ABOUT YOU?
HOW COMFORTABLE ARE YOU THAT YOU
WILL SURVIVE TONIGHT'S VOTE?
>> YOU KNOW, I CAME INTO THIS
GAME THINKING I WAS GOING TO
PLAY IT ONE WAY AND THEN
CIRCUMSTANCES HAD ME PLAY IT
ANOTHER WAY SO I WAS OUT OF THAT
COMFORT ZONE AND TRYING TO
IMPROVISE.
I'M TRYING TO MAYBE START
ANALYZING WHAT DID I DO RIGHT;
WHAT DID I DO WRONG.
BUT I THINK I MAY HAVE GOTTEN A
LITTLE TOO COMFORTABLE AT SOME
POINT.
MAYBE THAT WILL HURT ME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
JULIA, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON WILL BE ASKED TO
LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MICHAEL.
JULIA.
MICHAEL.
THREE VOTES MICHAEL; TWO VOTES
JULIA.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
WE HAVE A TIE.
WE'RE GOING DO REVOTE.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
MICHAEL AND JULIA, YOU WILL NOT
VOTE.
EVERYBODY ELSE, YOU CAN ONLY
VOTE FOR MICHAEL OR JULIA.
PHILLIP, IF YOU'LL GRAB THE URN.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JULIA.
JULIA.
TWO VOTES JULIA.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR" FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES, JULIA.
>> BYE SWEETIE.
>> THAT'S THREE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JULIA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> IT'S BEEN FUN.
GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE, HONEY.
>> Jeff: WELL, MICHAEL,
WRITING'S ON THE WALL.
YOU HAVE GOT YOUR WORK CUT OUT
FOR YOU.
>> (LAUGHS).
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR TORCHES,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
STAY TUNE FOR SCENES FOR OUR
NEXT EPISODE!
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR", A AMERICA SHAKES
THINGS UP, LEVELING THE PLAYING
FIELD.
>> NOW THERE'S AN INDIVIDUAL
GAME.
I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT EVERYBODY.
>> WELCOME ABOARD.
>> Jeff: AND EVERYONE IS
SURPRISED BY AN UNEXPECTED
FEAST.
>> IT'S A FOOD-EATING
COMPETITION.
>> YUCK!
(GAGGING)
>> OH, GOD.
>> THIS GAME WAS SO DIFFERENT
THAN I EXPECTED GOING INTO IT.
IT WAS TOUGH TO GO UP AGAINST A
VETERAN PLAYER, PEOPLE WHO KNEW
THE GAME INSIDE AND OUT AND WHO
PLAYED BEFORE AND BE AT THEIR
MERCY.
THAT'S ONE OF THE WORST FEELINGS
AT THIS GAME IS BEING AT THE
MERCY OF OTHER PEOPLE.
BUT I'VE HAD A WONDERFUL
EXPERIENCE ALTHOUGH IT'S BEEN
INCREDIBLY FRUSTRATING AT TIMES
AND I COULD HAVEN'T DON