"SURVIVOR" AFTER THE TRIBES
MERGED BIG MOVES OR ON
EVERYONE'S MIND BUT CORRINE AND
MALCOLM WERE PUTTING THEIRS INTO
ACTION.
>> WE CAN JUST QUIETLY TAKE OUT
SHERRI FIRST THEN TAKE FILL WILL
YOU PLEASE OUT.
HE'S THE HEAD OF THIS WHOLE
NONSENSE.
AS LONG AS PHILLIP GOES THAT
WHOLE ORGANIZATION WILL CRUMBLE.
>> Jeff: WITH PLANS TO BREAK
UP STEALTH "R" US THEY FORMED A
COUNTERALLIANCE MADE UP OF FANS
AND FAVORITES.
>> HE'S LIKE I HAVE REYNOLD AND
EDDIE, DO YOU HAVE MICHAEL?
I WAS LIKE, YUP, MICHAEL'S MIND.
>> OH, GOD!
>> Jeff: OF COCHRAN ATE UP THE
COMPETITION AT THE FIRST
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE --
COCHRAN PULLS IT OUT FOR
IMMUNITY!
SHERRI WAS THE TARGET OF THE
ENTIRE TRIBE BUT WHEN DAWN
CAUGHT WIND WITH THE SECRET
ALLIANCE WITH THE FANS STEALTH
"R" US HAD TO DECIDE BETWEEN AN
EASY TARGET OR A BIG MOVE.
>> I'M KIND OF UP FOR A LITTLE
BLIND SIDE.
IF SHE CAN PULL ALL THESE PEOPLE
WE'RE ALL SCREWED.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
THEY PULLED OFF THE BIGGEST MOVE
OF THE SEASON.
SEASON.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR" FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES, CORRINE, BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
>> VOTING OFF A MEMBER OF THEIR
ALLIANCE IN A SHOCKING BLIND
SIDE.
CORRINE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
11 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE IT, GUYS, 23
DAYS IN "SURVIVOR" WE GOT?
>> ARE WE AT 23 TODAY?
>> YUP, IT'S AMAZING.
>> 16 MORE TO GO.
>> WE ARE GOING TO DO IT BECAUSE
WE KNOW WE'RE SOLID WITH OUR
NUMBERS.
>> I NEED TO GO WASH MY FACE.
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE IT, BOYS.
>> AT LAST NIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL CORRINE GETS VOTED OUT.
I LOOK AT LAST NIGHT AS A
VICTORY.
>> WAY TO GO, GUYS!
>> EVEN THOUGH WE HAD THIS
COUNTERALLIANCE FORMING AND
CORRINE WAS A BIG PART OF OUR
COUNTERALLIANCE, AT THE END OF
THE DAY, CORRINE GOES HOME AND
IT'S NOT ME.
SO, LIKE, HAVE YOU NOTICED THAT
EVERY GIRL THAT ASSOCIATES
HERSELF WITH US GETS VOTED OUT?
>> I KNOW, NICE.
WHO'S THE NEXT VICTIM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M AT A POINT WHERE I HAVE
NOTHING TO LOSE.
I AM IRONCLAD MY GUYS WITH EDDIE
AND MALCOLM.
WE'RE UNWAIVERRINGLY TRUSTFUL TO
EACH OTHER.
SO IT'S JUST LIKE, YOU KNOW
WHAT?
I HAVE AN IDOL, I'M HERE, WE'RE
ALL SITTING AROUND, I'M GOING TO
PLAY THIS GAME.
SO WHAT'S YOUR GAME STRATEGY AT?
>> I'M PLAYING IT DAY BY DAY.
WHAT'S YOUR STRATEGY AT THIS
POINT?
>> I'M JUST OPENING THE DOOR.
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
>> (LAUGHS)
>> WITH CORRINE OUT OF THE GAME
I'VE LOST MY CLOSEST ALLY.
FLIP SIDE OF THAT IS NOW I'M THE
ONLY ONE NO WHO KNOWS ANT MY
IDOL.
I'M THE ONE THAT HAS THE ONLY
IDOL THAT KNOW ONE ELSE KNOWS IN
THIS GAME.
>> JUST KEEP SCRAMBLING.
IT'S FUN.
>> I THINK I'VE STILL GOT THE
FANS.
MIKE, EDDIE AND REYNOLD WILL GO
ALONG WITH ANYTHING I SAY SO I
TOOK A HIT LAST NIGHT BUT, YOU
KNOW, I'M STILL ALIVE.
THEY THOUGHT THEY'D CUT OFF THE
HEAD OF THIS SNAKE.
THEY THOUGHT THEY KILLED THE
REBEL LEADER, I GUESS.
THEY DON'T KNOW THEY MISSED YET.
>> TERM FIRST TIME I SAW YOU ON
THE BEACH I WAS LIKE DAMN, SHE'S
HOT.
>> THANK YOU.
HAS MIKE TRIED TO TALK TO YOU AT
ALL?
>> NO, HE KNOWS IT'S OVER AND
IT'S GOING TO BE SWEET REVENGE
WHEN THEY THOUGHT THEY COULD
TRAMPLE YOU, LADY.
TREAT MAMA IMPROPERLY AND NOW
LOOK WHAT HAPPENS.
EACH ONE OF THE FANS NEEDS TO
UNDERSTAND IF YOU DON'T DO WHAT
WE ASK YOU TO, YOU WILL GO HOME.
SHERRI IS WITH US IN TERMS OF
WHAT HER VOTING WILL BE AND SO
MIKE WILL GO HOME.
AS THE SPECIALIST, IT'S VERY
IMPORTANT THAT WHEN I ASSIGN YOU
A NAME, TENACITY.
ARE YOU PREPARED TO ACCEPT THE
NAME?
>> ABSOLUTELY, SIR.
>> THERE'S ONLY ONE REQUIREMENT
TO BELONG TO STEALTH "R" US.
YOU MUST BE LOYAL AND ABSOLUTELY
TRUSTWORTHY.
ARE YOU PREPARED TO DO THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> SHAKE MY HAND.
WELCOME TO THE ORGANIZATION.
>> BESIDES THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" I HAVE ANOTHER GAME
TO PLAY.
I HAVE TO PLAY THE SPECIALIST
GAME.
>> BRENDA THERE IS SERENITY.
WE ALSO HAVE MALCOLM, KNOWN AS
THE ENFORCER.
>> THERE'S FAKE ORGANIZATIONS,
THERE'S SECRET ALLIANCES, IT'S
ALL CRAZY.
(LAUGHS)
THEY'RE ALL CRAZY OUT HERE.
>> I HAVE NO INTENTIONS OF
VOTING YOU OUT OF THIS GAME.
WE'RE VERY CLOSE.
>> I AM WHOLEHEARTEDLY IN WITH
THE FAVORITES AND I AM GREAT
WITH BIG PERSONALITIES.
I HAD NO PROBLEM WITH SHEMAR, I
CAN HANDLE SHEMAR.
PHILLIP IS MY SHEMAR ON THIS
TRIBE.
YOU GIVE ME TWO MORE VOTES AND I
WILL BE CALLING SHOTS WITH
PHILLIP AND HE'LL BE COMING TO
ME ASKING ME WHAT I THINK AND
THAT'S MY PLAN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> OH!
>> Jeff: GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'LL DIVIDE INTO TWO TEAMS OF
FIVE.
ONE MEMBER OF EACH TEAM WILL BE
YOUR DEFENDER WHILE ONE AT A
TIME MEMBERS OF THE OTHER OTHER
TEAM LEAP OFF A PLATFORM AND
ATTEMPT TO THROW A BALL PAST
YOUR DEFENDER INTO THE NET.
EACH TIME YOU GET E A BALL IN
THE NET YOU SCORE A POINT FOR
YOUR TEAM.
FIRST TEAM TO FOUR WINS REWARD.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TEAM WILL
BE TAKEN FROM HERE TO A
BEAUTIFUL WATERFALL.
YOU WILL RAPPEL DOWN THE
WATERFALL.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: WAITING FOR YOU AT
THE BOTTOM, PICNIC LUNCH.
(APPLAUSE)
WE'RE GOING TO DIVIDE INTO TWO
TEAMS OF FIVE AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE FINISHED THE
SCHOOLYARD PICK.
EACH TEAM HAS ONE DEFENDER AND
FOUR SHOOTERS.
SHOOTING FOR THE PURPLE TEAM:
ERIC, EDDIE, REYNOLD AND
COCHRAN.
FOR THE ORANGE TEAM, DON,
PHILLIP AND, ANDREA, AND BRENDA.
OUT IN THE WATER GOT MALCOLM
DEFENDING FOR THE ORANGE TEAM,
MICHAEL WILL DEFEND FOR THE
PURPLE TEAM.
SHERRI WAS NOT PICKED, WILL NOT
GO ON REWARD.
EDDIE, FIRST UP FOR PURPLE.
>> WHO WANTS SOME?
>> Jeff: EDDIE RIGHT AT
MALCOLM!
NO LOVE FOR PURPLE.
SORRY, GUYS.
MICHAEL TAKES HIS SPOT, BRENDA
FOR ORANGE.
BRENDA LAUNCHED ONE AND IT'S IN!
ORANGE SCORES 1-ZIP.
ERIK GOING TO BE UP FOR PURPLE.
ERIK GOES HIGH AND SCORES!
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
UP NEXT, ANDREA.
SHE COULD PUT HER TEAM AHEAD 2-1
RIGHT HERE.
SHE GOES HIGH AND SHE SCORES!
ORANGE LEADS 2-1.
REYNOLD UP FOR PURPLE.
>> HEY!
>> Jeff: JUST SHORT.
NO SCORE.
>> Jeff: DAWN, THE OLDEST
WOMAN IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> COME ON, MAMA!
>> Jeff: DAWN FIRES ONE.
OH, JUST MISSES!
ORANGE STILL LEADS 2-1.
COCHRAN WON THE LAST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> GO, COCHRAN!
>> YOU GOT IT!
>> COCHRAN!
>> Jeff: COCHRAN IS ON A TEAR
IN CHALLENGES LATELY.
COCHRAN SCORES AND WE ARE TIED
2-2.
>> WHOO!
>> Jeff: UP NEXT, PHILLIP NOW
GOING TO TAKE ON MICHAEL.
>> COME ON, SPECIALIST.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, STUTTER STEP
GOES HIGH AND SCORES FOR ORANGE.
ORANGE LEADS 3-2.
EDDIE, BACK UP.
PURPLE WOULD LIKE TO TIE IT UP
RIGHT HERE.
HE GOES HIGH AND HE SCORES!
CLOSING THE GAP.
IT IS 3-3.
BRENDA.
ORANGE COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
>> YOU GOT THIS!
YOU GOT THIS!
SHE GOES HIGH!
JUST MISSES!
RIGHT ON THE EDGE, WOULDN'T GO
IN OPENING THE DOOR FOR THE
PURPLE TEAM.
MALCOLM ONCE AGAIN WITH THE
PRESSURE TO DEFEND.
ERIK, PURPLE COULD WIN IT RIGHT
HERE.
BIG REWARD, RAPPEL DOWN A
WATERFALL, PICNIC LUNCH, ONCE IN
A LIFETIME EXPERIENCE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY HE TOOK HIS
SNEAKERS OFF.
A MISTAKE!
>> Jeff: ERIK GOES HIGH AND HE
SCORES THE WINNING GOAL FOR
PURPLE!
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> Jeff: ERIK, EDDIE, COCHRAN,
REYNOLD AND MICHAEL GOING ON
REWARD!
>> I'M ON A WINNING TEAM!
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, ERIC,
COCHRAN, MICHAEL, EDDIE, NICE
JOB.
BIG REWARD.
YOU'LL RAPPEL DOWN THE FACE OF
THAT WATERFALL.
WAITING FOR YOU, A NICE PICNIC
LUNCH.
DAWN, PHILIP, ANDREA, MALCOLM,
BRENDA, SHERRI, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, ENJOY YOUR
REWARD.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
(APPLAUSE)
>> WE GET TO THE REWARD LOCATION
AND THERE'S THIS BRILLIANT
WATERFALL 40 OR SO FEET TALL AND
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO RAPPEL
DOWN IT.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO RAPPEL DOWN
IT.
THIS IS NOT SOMETHING I DO.
>> ONCE YOU'RE THERE LOOKING AT
THE WALL FOCUS ON THE WALL.
YOU CAN'T FOCUS ON THE DOWN.
YOU HAVE TO FOCUS ON THE WALL.
>> I RARELY LEAVE MY APARTMENT,
I RARELY LEAVE TWITTER AND THE
FACT THAT I'M GOING TO BE FLUNG
DOWN SOME WATERFALL ON A ROPE, I
DON'T EVEN KNOW THE MECHANICS OF
IT.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> KING OF THE WORLD!
>> YOU GUYS, YOU LOOK LIKE A
PRO.
>> ALL RIGHT, ERIK!
>> ERIK!
>> I'VE NEVER RAPPELED IN MY
LIFE SO I KIND OF THREW CAUTION
TO THE WIND AND JUST TRIED TO
JUMP DOWN THE THING LIKE JAMES
BOND.
IT WORKED OUT KIND OF WELL FOR
ME.
IT FELT KIND OF NATURAL.
>> I WATCHED MY TRIBE MATES GO
DOWN THE WATERFALL.
IT WASN'T MUCH CONSOLATION
BECAUSE I HAD NO IDEA WHAT THEY
WERE DOING BUT I'M LEARNING TO
EMBRACE IT.
THIS IS THE SAME GUY THAT WAS
AFRAID TO TAKE OFF HIS SHIRT THE
LAST TIME I PLAYED "SURVIVOR."
NOW I'M FLYING DOWN A WATERFALL
AFTER WINNING A CHALLENGE.
IT WAS FANTASTIC.
STILL A LITTLE BIT
NERVE-WRACKING.
I KIND OF SLID ON SOME MOSSY
ROCKS AND BUNGLED THE JOB A
LITTLE BIT BUT I LOVED IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS!
>> TUNA.
CLUBS.
>> THESE ARE AWESOME.
THANK YOU AGAIN FOR PICKING ME.
>> THIS WAS MEANT TO BE.
>> TO A GREAT AFTERNOON.
>> THERE WAS A TOTAL POST-BIG
WIN LOCKER ROOM GUYS MENTALITY
GOING ON AFTER THIS REWARD
CHALLENGE.
(BELCHING)
IT'S JUST SIMPLE, IT'S PURE.
EVERYTHING'S GOTTEN SO
COMPLICATED OUT HERE IT WAS A
GREAT REPRIEVE FOR ALL OF US.
>> THE LAST FANS VERSUS FAVORITE
WAS DOMINATED BY WOMEN IN THE
END.
HOW COOL WOULD IT BE IF IT WAS
DOMINATED BY GUYS.
>> HOPE'S GONE SO THERE'S NOBODY
WORTH (BLEEP)ING ANYWAYS.
>> SERIOUSLY, COCHRAN, THREE
WARRIORS, THREE UNITED VOTES.
WE'RE A UNITED BLOCK.
THE PITCH TO COCHRAN WAS LET'S
TAKE THE MUSCLE TO THE END.
LET DEESE THIS ALL GUY'S
ALLIANCE.
LET'S BRO DOWN, GET THE SCHEMING
CRAZY GIRLS THAT KEEP FLIRTING
WITH ALL OF US OUT OF HERE AND
TAKE THE STRONG GUYS TO THE END.
>> "SURVIVOR" IS ALL ABOUT WHO'S
-- YOU KNOW, A HANDFUL OF
LEGENDARY MOVES PEOPLE HAVE
NEVER FORGOTTEN.
YOU WANT TO BE ONE OF THEM.
>> "SURVIVOR" BIG MOMENTS.
I LIKE THAT.
>> REYNOLD, EDDIE AND MICHAEL
MUST NOT KNOW ME IF THEY THINK
THAT EMPHASIZING THE
TESTOSTERONE UNITY BETWEEN US
AND WE'RE MEN, WE'RE MEN AND WE
WAIT WOMEN AND WE'RE GOING TO
SLAP EACH OTHER WITH TOWELS IN
THE LOCKER ROOM AND CHUG BEERS.
THAT DOESN'T WORK WITH ME.
THAT DOESN'T APPEAL TO ME AT
ALL.
>> ALL RIGHT US!
I WON'T BE ENGAGING IN ANY
MASCULINE TOM FOOLERY WITH THESE
NUMSKULLS.
>> WELL, WE TRIED.
>> WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE,
WE DON'T NEED A PARANOIA DAY.
>> WE LOSE THE REWARD-- SAW IT
COMING A MILE AWAY, GOT OVER
PRETTY QUICK BECAUSE WHILE I
DIDN'T GET TO GO ON A REWARD I
WAS WITH THE PEOPLE I NEEDED TO
BE AROUND.
I NEED NUMBERS AND IT'S EASIEST
TO SCOOP UP THE PEOPLE ON THE
BOTTOM AND SHERRI AND DAWN SEEM
LIKE THE MOST LIKELY CANDIDATES
TO ME.
WE'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
BEST CASE IF WE STAY IS THAT
MIKE, REYNOLD AND EDEDLY GO
FIRST.
IF WE DO IT WE DON'T REALLY NEED
MORE THAN FIVE.
IF THEY THINK WE'RE IN ON IT
THEY'LL SPLIT THE VOTE: FOUR
REYNOLD; FOUR EDDIE AND THEN
WE'RE GUARANTEED FINAL FIVE.
>> FAVORITES THINK THEY HAVE
EIGHT PEOPLE.
THEY THINK IT'S THE SEVEN
REMAINING FAVORITES AND THEY'VE
BROUGHT IN SHERRI FOR EIGHT
AGAINST THREE WHICH WOULD BE
MIKE, REYNOLD AND EDDIE.
I'M OEUPBG TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
THAT BECAUSE IF THEY GO WITH
THAT AND I CAN PULL IN A
FIVE-PERSON ALLIANCE THAT'S
ENOUGH TO TAKE OVER THE GAME.
WE'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
>> RIGHT.
>> IF WE ARE GOING TO DO
SOMETHING IT HAS TO BE NOW.
>> YEAH, BUT HOW?
>> THERE'S SIX PEOPLE IF YOU'RE
IN.
>> YOU'RE SAYING USE THE FOUR
FANS --
>> THEY'RE ALREADY IN, SHERRI
JUST AGREED.
BUT WE ALL HAVE TO DO IT.
>> RIGHT.
MALCOLM'S COME TO ME AND SAID
HERE'S HOW I WANT TO VOTE.
HERE'S WHO I'LL WORK WITH.
DO YOU WANT TO COME ON BOARD?
AND I'M THINKING HE'S GOING TO
BE A PROBLEM.
LET ME TALK TO SHERRI, LET ME
THINK AND THEN TALK TO YOU.
IT WOULD BE GREAT IF I COULD
GIVE HIM THE IMPRESSION I WAS
VOTING WITH HIM AND WE COULD ALL
JUST TAKE HIM OUT.
MALCOLM APPROACHED ME AND SAID
HE HAS FOUR GUYS AND ME, THAT'S
WHAT THEY NEED.
AND THE WAY THEY WOULD WANT TO
DO IT WOULD BE THAT YOU GUYS
WOULD SPLIT THE VOTES FOR EDDIE
AND REYNOLD AND THAT WE WOULD
HAVE FIVE.
>> HE'S TRYING TO FLIP IT.
>> DID HE SAY SOMETHING TO YOU?
>> YEAH, HE WANTS ME TO FLIP
WITH SHERRI.
>> WHAT?
>> YUP.
>> I THINK WE TELL HIM WE'RE
SPLITTING THE VOTES, WE MAKE HIM
THINK THAT HE'S PULLING THIS
GREAT BLIND SIDE, HE'S GOING TO
THINK HE'S AMAZING.
>> WHICH MEANS SHERRI AND I HAVE
TO GO ALONG.
>> YOU TELL HIM WE'RE GOING
ALONG WITH IT, WE ALL JUST VOTE
MALCOLM OUT.
>> MALCOLM HAS BEEN TRYING TO
PLAY DOUBLE DUTY.
HE'S BEEN TRYING TO PLAY ME AS
IF HE WAS STILL PART OF THE CORE
ALLIANCE.
ME, THE SPECIALIST.
>> WHAT'S THE WORD?
>> WE'RE GOING TO DO A SPLIT FOR
EDDIE AND REYNOLD.
HE'S GOING TO BE THINKING WE'RE
VOTING FOR REYNOLD AND EDDIE
WHEN, IN FACT, WE'RE GOING TO BE
VOTING FOR HIM.
NOTHING TO DO IT'S KIND OF NICE
TO GET AWAY AND I FELT LIKE I
WAS A LITTLE KID SNEAKING OUT
FROM MY PARENTS' HOUSE AGAIN
WHEN EDDIE AND I WENT TO THE
LAGOON AND EDDIE'S REALLY HOT
SO, LIKE, MAYBE WE'RE DATING, I
DON'T KNOW IF THIS IS ISLAND
DATING, I'M NOT SURE.
BUT THE MORE I PLAY UP THIS
POSSIBLE EDDIE RELATIONSHIP THE
MORE LIKELY HE IS TO MAYBE VOTE
FOR ME IN THE END OR GIVE ME
INFORMATION.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU THINKING.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> I MEAN, I'LL DO WHATEVER I
NEED TO DO, I GUESS, IS WHAT I'M
SAYING.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR VOTE OUT
REYNOLD.
>> YOU PROMISE?
>> PROMISE WHAT?
>> YOU'LL VOTE THE WAY I SAY?
>> YEAH.
WHAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M NOT PLAYING YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> GET RID OF ME, MIKE, AND
REYNOLD YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
GET RID OF THE THREE FANS.
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN AFTER
THAT WITH YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> UH-HUH.
I TRUST YOU BUT I DON'T TRUST
THE OTHER PEOPLE THAT ARE WITH
YOU.
>> I'M SAYING I COULD BE AN
ASSET TO YOU.
THAT'S WHEY WHAT I'M SAYING.
>> BUT YOU WON'T VOTE AGAINST
REYNOLD.
WILL YOU VOTE AGAINST MALCOLM?
>> IF I HAVE TO.
WHAT'S TROUBLING TO ME IS I
DON'T THINK ANDREA WANTS TO VOTE
ME OUT.
I THINK SHE WANTS TO KEEP ME
HERE.
I THINK SHE LIKES ME AND I THINK
SHE REALLY DOES WANT TO DRAG ME
ALONG IN THIS GAME AND I JUST
NEED TO BE DRAGGED TWO OR THREE
MORE VOTES BEFORE I CAN GET UP
ON MY OWN FEET AND START
PUNCHING PEOPLE.
>> I MEAN, DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT IDOLS.
>> NO, I REALLY DON'T.
>> HONESTLY?
>> NOPE.
>> IF YOU CAN GIVE ME
INFORMATION ON WHAT MALCOLM IS
SUGGESTING AND JUST TO ME I CAN
AT LEAST GUARANTEE THAT NEXT
VOTE WON'T BE YOU AND THEN WE
CAN WORK VOTE TO VOTE AND I CAN
TRY TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO SNEAK
YOU BY.
I'D VOTE FOR YOU IF YOU'RE IN
THE TOP THREE.
I LIKE YOU.
>> I DON'T SEE MYSELF GOING THAT
FOR.
>> SERIOUSLY, YOU DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHO GOES OUT HERE
AND ACTUALLY FALLS FOR SOMEONE.
THAT'S REALLY RARE.
NORMALLY THERE'S AN ELEMENT OF
PLAYING SOMEBODY.
SO I KNOW I'M PLAYING EDDIE BUT
I'M SEEING IF HE'S TRYING TO
PLAY ME.
WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT YOU CAME
TO ME.
>> EVEN THOUGH IT'S A GAME I
STILL ONLY LIKE TALKING TO
CERTAIN PEOPLE, YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN?
>> (LAUGHS)
>> I AM INDIRECTLY HITTING ON
YOU.
>> (LAUGHS)
COULDN'T TELL.
>> Jeff: GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: TODAY'S CHALLENGE IS
GOING TO TEST YOUR ABILITY TO
REMAIN CALM WHEN EVERYTHING ELSE
IN YOUR BODY URGES YOU TO DO
OTHERWISE.
YOU'LL EACH TAKE A SPOT IN THE
WATER UNDERNEATH A GRATED STEEL
BARRIER.
AS THE TIDE RISES THE WATER WILL
RISE.
AS THE WATER RISES, YOUR SPACE
TO BREATHE WILL DECREASE UNTIL
YOU RUN OUT.
THE PERSON WHO LASTS THE LONG
NEST THIS CHALLENGE WINS
IMMUNITY, IS GUARANTEED A 1-10
SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
ALL RIGHT, COCHRAN, I HAVE LET
YOU HOLD ON TO THAT NECKLACE AS
LONG AS I CAN.
IF YOU'LL SWIM IT OVER TO ME AND
EVERYBODY CAN TAKE YOUR SPOTS
WE'LL GET STARTED.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
EVERYBODY SLIDE UNDER THE GRATE.
THIS CHALLENGE IS OFFICIALLY ON.
>> THIS IS THIS SUCKS ALREADY.
>> THIS IS HOW WE'D BE SPENDING
OUR DAY BACK AT CAMP ANYWAYS,
JUST FLOATING IN THE WATER.
IT'S GOING TO BE A LOT MORE
DIFFICULT.
THAT TIDE IS STARTING TO RISE.
IT'S SLOW BUT IT'S STEADY.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE RUNNING OUT
OF SPACE.
THE WATER HAS RISEN ABOUT THREE
INCHES.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO START
FEELING IT NIP AT YOU'RES.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE NOW BEEN OUT
HERE ONE HOUR.
THE WATER IS NOW INCHING TOWARD
THE ONE-INCH MARK.
SLOWLY YOU ARE RUNNING OUT OF
SPACE.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO BE TESTED.
NOW COMES THE PART OF THE
CHALLENGE WHERE YOU NEED TO
REMAIN CALM THE WATER NOW
STARTING TO CREST ABOVE THAT
GRATE.
PHILLIP IS THE FIRST PERSON OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
TAKE A SPOT UP THERE ON THE
PLATFORM.
WE ARE DOWN TO TEN.
THE BIGGEST OBSTACLE IN THIS
CHALLENGE IS GOING TO BE YOUR
SENSE OF PANIC.
SHERRI, SECOND PERSON OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
AND ERIK IS THE THIRD PERSON OUT
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO EIGHT.
DAWN STRUGGLING TO STAY IN THIS.
TAKING ON A LOT OF WATER.
DAWN OPTS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
THE FOURTH PERSON OUT OF THIS
CHANNEL.
>> THOSE WAVES SUCK.
>> (COUGHING).
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY HAVING TO
MAKE SOME SORT OF A SNORKEL
USING THEIR HANDS WHILE TRYING
NOT TO TAKE ON TOO MUCH WATER
AND NOT PANICKING WHEN THEY DO.
IT'S A LOT.
MALCOLM IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
>> YOU DID SO GOOD!
>> Jeff: MIKE, STRUGGLING
TRYING TO STAY IN THIS.
>> LOOK AT MIKE FALLING APART.
>> Jeff: OH, GEEZ, HE'S OUT.
GOOD JOB, MIKE.
>> Jeff: MICHAEL'S OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE!
>> HANG ON FOR A SECOND YOU'RE
GOING TO BE DIZZY.
>> Jeff: IT IS COCHRAN,
REYNOLD, BRENDA, EDDIE AND
ANDREA.
THE WATER NOW ABOVE THE GRATE.
EDDIE'S TAKING IN A LOT OF
WATER.
COCHRAN NOW STARTING TO PANIC.
REYNOLD UNDERWATER, WILL HE COME
BACK UP?
EDDIE'S OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
COCHRAN'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE,
REYNOLD IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
>> THE GIRLS!
>> Jeff: JUST LIKE THAT WE ARE
DOWN TO TWO IN A MATTER OF THREE
SECONDS THE THREE REMAINING GUYS
OPTED OUT.
IT IS BRENDA AND ANDREA.
BRENDA HAS NOT MOVED SINCE THIS
CHALLENGE STARTED.
HER LEG HAS BEEN DRAPED.
ANDREA'S LEGS HAVE BEEN DRAPED
SINCE THIS CHALLENGE STARTED.
WE'LL KNOW THE PANIC IS COMING
WHEN THE LEGS START TO MOVE.
ANDREA STRUGGLING A BIT BUT
STILL IN IT.
BRENDA STILL CALM.
ANDREA STRUGGLING SOME MORE.
THERE GO THE LEGS.
AND SHE'S BACK IN IT!
ANDREA STILL IN IT!
STILL FIGHTING!
IS SHE GOING TO COME BACK UP?
NO, ANDREA'S OUT.
BRENDA WINS IMMUNITY!
SOMEBODY LET HER KNOW.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
BRENDA, YOU GOOD TO SWIM OVER
HERE?
COME GET IT.
(APPLAUSE)
BRENDA SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
GUARANTEED A 1-10 SHOT AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
THE REST OF YOU AFTER 25 DAYS
SOMEBODY'S GOING HOME TONIGHT.
TKPWR-B YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> Jeff: WAY TO GO, BRENDA!
LOOKS GOOD ON YOU, YOU EARNED
THAT BABY.
>> YOU HAD ONE LEG THROUGH.
YOU LOOKED LIKE YOU WAS ON A
VACATION.
I'M JUST KICKING BACK HERE,
BABY, ALL DAY LONG.
>> THIS NEXT VOTE HAS TO BE THE
TURNING POINT IN THE GAME THAT
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
IT'S THE LAST TIME THAT I
DEFINITELY CAN'T HAVE THE
NUMBERS ON MY SIDE.
I WAIT ANY LONGER, REYNOLD,
EDDIE, MIKE ARE GOING TO BE
GONE.
THEY'RE EASY PICKINGS FOR VOTES
RIGHT NOW.
THE FAVORITES HAVE TO THINK I'M
100% WITH THEM OR THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO SPLIT THE VOTE.
SO I'VE SAT ON THE BOTTOM FOR 25
DAYS AND I'M GOING TO MAKE MY
MOVE ON TOP.
>> SO IT'S FOUR GIRLS AND
REYNOLD, FOUR GUYS AND EDDIE AND
WE GET REYNOLD.
>> BUT ON THE SECOND VOTE --
>> IT'S REYNOLD NO MATTER WHAT.
>> REYNOLD NO MATTER WHAT.
>> I'M SO TIRED.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> RAN OFF, HAD A CHAT WITH
ANDREA.
SHE'S CALLING THE SHOTS, I NEED
HER TO THINK I'M ON BOARD WITH
HER PLAN AND HER TRUSTING ME
WITH THAT PLAN MEANS SHE DOESN'T
SUSPECT WHAT'S GOING ON.
WHAT I HAVE UP MY SLEEVE.
>> MALCOLM'S A GOOD LIAR.
I'M LYING TO HIM; HE'S LYING TO
ME.
JUST THIS WHOLE DYNAMIC OF IT IS
PRETTY HILARIOUS.
NOW HE'S TRYING TO PULL DAWN
OVER AND DAWN IS WORKING IT.
DAWN IS THE M.V.P. OF THE -- I
DON'T KNOW WHERE THIS DAWN CAME
FROM.
AFTER NEW DAWN IS -- SHE'S GOOD
AT THIS.
>> OKAY, YOU WANT TO TAKE OUT
FILL TRIP?
>> NO.
>> WHO DO YOU WANT TO TAKE OUT?
>> ANDREA.
>> OKAY.
>> ANDREA IS THE LEADER OUT
HERE.
AS MUCH AS PHILLIP HAS BLUSTER
AND AS MUCH AS THESE GUYS ARE
UPSET WITH HIM, HE'S NOT RUNNING
THINGS, HE'S KIND OF A JOKE.
WHEN YOU'RE TRYING TO STIR A POT
INSIDE A REBELLION, YOU DON'T
KILL THE PRINCE, YOU KILL THE
PERSON ACTUALLY RUNNING THE SHOW
WHICH IS ANDREA.
I WANT TO PLAY THIS GAME TO THE
END.
IF WE DON'T DO IT NOW WE DON'T
HAVE THE CHANCE AND REYNOLD HAS
AN IDOL.
>> IF YOU SHOW ME THE IDOL THEN
I'LL DO IT.
BUT I'M NEVER GOING TO BE ABLE
TO LOOK IN THE EYE AGAIN.
>> I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
TONIGHT.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
IT'S NUT IT IS FACT THAT I'M
COMING BACK AFTER CORRINE'S VOTE
AND MALCOLM IS STILL TRUSTING ME
WHEN I'M THE PERSON THAT GAVE
THE INFORMATION ON CORRINE TELLS
ME THAT HE'S NOT DIALED IN.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> AND THEN DO WE KNOW IF
THEY'RE GOING SPLIT THE VOTE?
>> THEY'RE DEFINITELY SPLITTING
THE VOTE.
>> BETWEEN WHO?
>> YOU AND EDDIE.
DOESN'T MATTER, THOUGH, THEY
HAVE FOUR ME AND DAWN WITH WITH
YOU, DONE, NO IDOL HAS TO BE
PLAYED SHE JUST WANTS TO KNOW
THAT WE HAVE IT BECAUSE THE NEXT
VOTE WILL BE HARRY.
>> WHO ARE WE VOTING?
>> ANDREA.
>> YES!
ANDREA.
OKAY.
>> GIVE ME A HAND SHAKE ON IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THERE'S ROOM FOR ONE MORE.
I JUST HAVE LESS ABILITY TO MOVE
OVER.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, MY GOSH, I'M SO BEAT.
ALL RIGHT, COOL.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
>> IF YOU DON'T FOLLOW THROUGH I
GO HOME TONIGHT.
SO DON'T SCREW ME.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> IF I HAVE REASON TO DOUBT YOU
I'M GOING TO PLAY IT FOR MYSELF
TONIGHT.
>> RIGHT.
NO, I UNDERSTAND THAT.
I CAN'T STAND PEOPLE THAT
INTIMIDATE OTHER PEOPLE AND I
THINK REYNOLD IS USED TO BEING
IN CONTROL AND GETTING WHAT HE
WANT BUT HE DID SHOW ME THE
IDOL, WHICH IS HUGE.
I MEAN NOW I HAVE MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT HOW TO VOTE
AND WHAT TO DO.
BUT, I MEAN, HE LOOKED OVER AND
SAID "IF YOU BURN ME YOU'LL HAVE
HELL TO PAY."
AND I FEEL LIKE SHAME ON YOU,
SHOULD HAVEN'T SHOWN ME YOUR
IDOL.
SHAME ON YOU, MALCOLM.
YOU SHOULD HAVEN'T BROUGHT ME
IN.
>> SHE SAT DOWN -- I SAT DOWN
NEXT TO HER, I SHOWED HER THE
IDOL.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> AND SHE SAID "OKAY."
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M NERVOUS
ABOUT.
>> YEAH, OF COURSE.
>> NOT FOLLOWING THROUGH WITH
IT.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'M GOING TO TALK TO ANDREA.
>> DUDE SHE CHANGES HER MIND
EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
>> I KNOW.
>> SHE PROMISES YOU THE WORLD.
SHE'S DANGEROUS, DUDE.
YOU'RE GOING TO FALL INTO A TRAP
WITH HER.
>> I KNOW.
>> LET'S JUST GET HER OUT OF
HERE AND THEN COCHRAN WILL
PROBABLY WARM UP TO US AND BRO
DOWN WITH THE GUYS TO THE END.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IS THAT HAPPENING?
>> MAYBE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE SPLITTING FOR
ME AND REYNOLD ONE OF US IS
GOING HOME.
>> I CAN TELL YOU IT'S NOT YOU
AND REYNOLD.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE IT'S NOT WORKING WITH
REYNOLD I'M WORKING WITH YOU.
>> REYNOLD IS WORKING WITH ME.
>> I'M JUST SAYING IT'S NOT YOU.
>> WHO ARE YOU VOTING FOR?
I DON'T GET IT.
ARE YOU VOTING FOR MIKE?
>> MAYBE.
>> IF YOU TELL ME I'LL VOTE THAT
WAY AND I PROMISE YOU I WON'T
MAKE A MOVE.
>> 100% I CAN'T.
100% YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME.
>> CAN YOU TELL ME IT'S MIKE OR
MALCOLM?
>> IT'S NOT MALCOLM.
>> IT IS REYNOLD?
>> DO YOU WANT TO BE SAFE OR
NOT?
>> I WANT TO BE SAFE BUT I DON'T
WANT TO LOSE REYNOLD.
WHAT?
>> JUST TRUST ME.
>> IF REYNOLD PLAYS AN IDOL
TONIGHT I GO HOME.
>> IS HE GOING TO PLAY AN IDOL.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DOES HE HAVE AN IDOL.
>> SOMEBODY HERE DOES.
>> YOU SAID YOU KNOW HE DOESN'T
HAVE AN IDOL.
>> I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
AS OF RIGHT NOW I DON'T KNOW
ANYMORE.
>> WELL IF MALCOLM REALLY IS
BETRAYING ME AND THINKS HE HAS
FIVE OR SIX IT COULD BE ME, I I
GUESS.
>> IT COULD BE YOU.
>> OR WHOEVER.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO WHY CAN'T YOU LET ME IN?
>> IF MY NAME COMES UP LET ME
KNOW.
RIGHT NOW IT'S FINE.
>> IT'S BEEN TALKED ABOUT.
>> ME?
>> YEAH!
AND THAT'S WHY I'M TRYING TO RUN
AROUND WITH REYNOLD, WE'RE
TRYING TO AVOID THAT.
>> I'M GOING HOME TONIGHT!
THIS IS, LIKE, MALCOLM'S
TARGETING ME AND NOW I HAVE TO
THINK OF A WAY TO -- THERE'S AN
IDOL SO I HAVE TO COME UP WITH A
WAY TO CHANGE EVERYTHING UP AND
I DON'T -- UGH.
I MAY BE GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> OKAY, WHAT ARE WE CHANGING?
>> WE HAVE TO GO WITH THE SAFE
VOTE AND GO WITH MICHAEL.
>> OKAY, IF YOU'RE IN DANGER,
YEAH.
I'M FINE DOING MICHAEL.
FRANKLY, I WAS A LITTLE BIT
TURNED OFF THAT ANDREA WAS SO
WILLING TO ABANDON WHAT I THINK
WAS THE SMARTEST AGGRESSIVE MOVE
IN TAKING OUT MALCOLM TONIGHT.
>> I MEAN, THE SAFEST BET EVER
WOULD BE MICHAEL.
>> I STILL LIKE MALCOLM.
>> I KNOW BUT YOU'RE NOT -- I
THINK I'M BEING TARGETED.
>> SHE'S COMPLETELY CHANGED HER
MIND NOW SUDDENLY WE HAVE TO GO
FOR THE SAFE VOTE WHICH WOULD BE
TO VOTE OUT MICHAEL BECAUSE
MICHAEL, UNLIKE ANYBODY ELSE,
HAS PROVEN TIME AND TIME AGAIN
IN TRIBAL COUNCIL NOT TO HAVE AN
IDOL.
>> WE ARE ABSOLUTELY -- ALL THE
WORK I DID TODAY IS COMPLETELY
DOWN THE DRAIN.
ALL OF IT'S GOING TO BE GONE.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> I PROMISE YOU MALCOLM DOESN'T
HAVE THE IDOL.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S OUR CHANCE TO
TAKE MALCOLM OUT!
LIKE WE HAD A CHANCE, WE HAD A
PLAN, WE COULD HAVE TOLD
EVERYBODY AND JUST DONE IT!
>> I KNOW BUT IT WAS --
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE WORRIED
BECAUSE EDDIE GOT INVOLVED AND
MADE YOU FEEL LIKE YOU WERE
GOING HOME AND I'M TELLING YOU
HE WASN'T IN CHARGE OF THAT
VOTE, IT WAS HAPPENING!
I FELT FEEL LIKE MY WHOLE GAME
IS LOST NOW.
>> IF YOU REALLY HONESTLY THINK
THAT -- IF YOU HONESTLY -- IF
YOU HONESTLY THINK THAT
MALCOLM'S NOT GOING TO HAVE AN
IDOL PLAYED ON HIM, IF WE'RE
CHANGING THE PLAN TEN MINUTES TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND IT'S JUST YOU
AND ME DOING EVERYTHING --
>> I FEEL LIKE THE THREE GUYS
DON'T HAVE IMMUNITY TONIGHT WITH
THAT ONE IDOL AND WE'RE THINKING
MICHAEL.
>> HONESTLY --
>> I HAD SOMEONE SHOW ME AN IDOL
TODAY.
JUST TO PROVE THAT WE WERE SAFE.
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN -- I MEAN, I CAN CHANGE
IT.
IT AS A GLIMMER OF HOPE THAT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL IT
WASN'T A FAN THAT WAS VOTED OUT?
IT WAS A FAVORITE?
>> YES, I MEAN, I WAS A LITTLE
IN SHOCK BUT ALSO I WAS, LIKE,
OH, WELL, THIS IS WHAT I HAD
HOPED WOULD HAPPEN, SOME OF THE
FAVORITES WOULD START TO SEE
EACH OTHER AS THREATS AND START
TO USE SOME OF THE FANS
UNFORTUNATELY THEY DIDN'T USE ME
FOR THAT VOTE BUT THEY CAN USE
ME FOR OTHER VOTES.
>> BUG.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP, WHAT DO YOU
SEE GOING ON AT CAMP?
>> WELL, FROM THE BEGINNING
FAVORITES GOT TOGETHER AND WE
DECIDED THAT WE WOULD DEVELOP A
STRATEGY AND THAT STRATEGY
INCORPORATED STEALTH "R" US.
A VERY EFFECTIVE ORGANIZATION,
SOMETHING THAT I INTRODUCED IN
SEASON 22 "SURVIVOR" REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
AND WE HAVE A NEWER MEMBER, A
VERY, VERY EFFECTIVE DOUBLE
AGENT WHO'S ABLE TO SHARE A
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF OPERATIVE
INFORMATION IN THE FORM OF
SHERRI AND HER NAME IS TENACITY.
I GAVE HER THAT NAME BECAUSE SHE
HAS A UNIQUE CAPABILITY OF
HOLDING ON IN THIS GAME, MOST
LIKELY MUCH FURTHER THAN ANY OF
THE OTHER FANS.
>> Jeff: MICHAEL, SO IT'S
REALLY YOU, REYNOLD, AND EDDIE.
SHERRI IS CLEARLY NOW A MEMBER
OF STEALTH "R" US.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER THEY ALL
VOTED FOR ME, ALL MY T FANS
WROTE MY NAME DOWN.
PAYBACK'S A BITCH.
>> Jeff: EDDIE, CONCERN YOU?
>> IT DOESN'T REALLY BOTHER ME
THAT MUCH NOW TO BE HONEST.
I'M ONE OF THREE TO GO ANYWAY
AND I'D RATHER PLAY MY OWN GAME
THAN BE SOMEBODY ELSE'S PUPPET
OR IN THEIR LITTLE LEAGUE OF
OPERATIVES.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, LITTLE
CONCERNED ABOUT PHILLIP AND HIS
OPERATIVES?
>> IT'S EIGHT OPERATIVES AGAINST
THREE NEW KIDS ON THE BLOCK THAT
CAME IN TO THEIR HOME CAMP.
>> Jeff: BUT IF SOMEBODY HAS
AN IDOL ON THE ENEMY SIDE AND
THINGS WORK OUT AND THEY PLAY IT
AT THE RIGHT TIME IT COULD FLIP
THE GAME.
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
>> EXCUSE ME, JEFF, WE ALREADY
KNOW FROM MY PRIOR SEASON THAT I
DISCUSSED THAT IF WE THINK YOU
HAVE AN IDOL YOU WILL BE VOTED
FOR.
>> Jeff: MICHAEL, LITTLE
CONCERNED?
>> AT THIS POINT, YOU KNOW, I'M
READY TO PLAY WITH SOMEBODY WHO
ACTUALLY WANTS TO PLAY.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE SAYING IF
AND WHEN THIS STEALTH "R" US
BEGINS TO BREAK DOWN I'LL BE
HERE SO --
>> IT ALREADY HAS BEGUN TO BREAK
DOWN.
THEY VOTED OUT CORRINE BEFORE
THEY VOTED OUT A FAN.
>> WELL WE ALSO KNOW THAT FROM
AGAIN -- I HATE TO KEEP
REPEATING MYSELF, SEASON 22,
REDEMPTION ISLAND THAT, IN FACT,
A COALITION THAT STICKS TOGETHER
ACTUALLY GETS TO THE END
TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, IS THAT THE
BIG QUESTION?
THAT, YEAH, WE CAN STEUG
TOGETHER BUT WE CAN'T ALL GO TO
THE END.
SO AT SOME POINT SOMEONE WILL
MAKE A MOVE AND WIN.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT THE
DILEMMA IS.
FROM MY SEASON I WAS ON THE
BOTTOM OF MY ALLIANCE, I DIDN'T
KNOW IT AT THE TIME BUT IF YOU
HAVE A SENSE THAT YOU'RE ON THE
BOTTOM THIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
FLIP BECAUSE YOU DO HAVE THREE
FANS AND MAYBE OTHERS AMONG THE
STEALTH "R" US ORGANIZATION AS
WELL THAT ARE READY TO MAKE
MOVES AND TOTALLY CHANGE THE
GAME.
>> Jeff: SO WHEN ANDREA SAYS
IF THE RIGHT PERSON GETS THE
RIGHT NUMBERS AT THE RIGHT TIME
THEY CAN CHANGE THE GAME.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, I FULLY
EXPECT THAT TO HAPPEN.
BUT I BELIEVE AT THIS TIME IF
SOMEONE WERE TO OPERATE RIGHT
NOW WITH IMPUNITY AND DECIDE,
WELL, THIS IS THE RIGHT TIME
BECAUSE OF WHATEVER THEIR REASON
IS I THINK THEY'RE GOING TO FIND
THAT THEY ACTUALLY ERRED IN
THEIR JUDGMENT BECAUSE THERE'S
ENOUGH NUMBERS STILL LESS AND
ENOUGH SMART PEOPLE STILL HERE
THEY'LL FIGURE THAT OUT.
SO WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS A BRAVE
MOVE, YOU'LL GET FLUSHED OUT,
GOOD-BYE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
PHILLIP, YOU'RE UP.
>> THIS IDEA WAS THIS WAS A
THROWAWAY VOTE.
AFTER PHILLIP'S LITTLE SPEECH I
DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
ANYMORE.
HOPEFULLY THINGS GO ACCORDING TO
PLAN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> HOLD UP.
THEY ALL VOTED FOR ME.
YOU CAN TELL, THAT WHOLE STORY
WAS ABOUT, GIVE IT TO ME, I'M IN
GOOD SHAPE.
I'M BEING DEAD SERIOUS RIGHT
NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: SO REYNOLD GAVE HIS
IDOL TO MALCOLM.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR MALCOLM WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ANDREA.
ANDREA.
THREE VOTES ANDREA.
REYNOLD.
THREE VOTES ANDREA, ONE VOTE
MICHAEL.
FIVE VOTES MICHAEL; THREE VOTES
ANDREA, ONE VOTE REYNOLD.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
MICHAEL, THAT'S SIX, THAT'S
ENOUGH, YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
MICHAEL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> YOU TURKEYS.
>> Jeff: WELL, THERE ARE TEN
VERY SALVERY PLAYERS LEFT AND
ONLY ONE THING YOU CAN RELY ON,
YOUR GUT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
>> (BAWLING).
>> Jeff: AS THE END GETS
CLOSER, THE PRESSURE BUILDS.
AND SOMEONE'S GOING TO BREAK.
>> IT'S BAFFLING TO ME.
SHE'S ACTING LIKE A LUNATIC.
>> I'LL PULL MYSELF FROM THE
GAME, I'M NOT KIDDING.
>> IT HAS BEEN A LONG, STRANGE,
WEIRD, DIFFICULT JOURNEY.
IT'S OVER, WHAT CAN I SAY.
I'M VERY DISAPPOINTED.
I WANTED TO GO FAR AND DEEP INTO
THE GAME AND I THOUGHT I COULD
BUT THE FAVORITES ARE GREAT
PLAYERS, THEY'RE TIGHT AND
THEY'RE PLAYING HARD AND STRONG.
I KNOW IT'S GOING TO BUST UP
EVENTUALLY BUT HERE I AM.
IT'S BUMMER.