>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AT THE FANS CAMP,
EVERYTHING WAS UPSIDE DOWN.
THE STRONG WERE ON THE BOTTOM.
>> IN A TIGHT SPOT NOW.
>> I THOUGHT WE WERE ON THE SAME
PAGE ABOUT VOTING SHAMAR OFF.
>CON
TKPWRATS TO THEM, THEY GOT US.
>> Jeff: WHILE THE ALLIANCE OF
THE WEAK CONTROLLED THE GAME.
>> IT'S REVENGE OF THE NERDS.
>> Jeff: WHAT THEY COULDN'T
CONTROL WAS THEIR ALLY SHAMAR.
>> I'M NOT A QUITTER BUT THESE
ARE CHILDISH, IMMATURE GAMES.
>> Jeff: HE THREATENED TO
QUIT.
>> I COME HERE AND EVERYTHING IS
SHAMAR'S DOING THIS, SHAMAR'S
DOING THAT.
>> Jeff: BUT SHERRI AND LAURA
CONVINCED HIM TO STAY.
>> WE'LL BE DOWN TWO IF YOU
QUIT.
LOYALTY MEANS EVERYTHING TO ME.
I'LL STAY AND FIGHT.
>> Jeff: AT THE FAVORITES
CAMP, EVERYTHING WAS WORKING
OUT.
>> ALL I NEED IS AN AUDIENCE.
>> Jeff: SPIRITS WERE HIGH.
>> EVERY SINGLE SECOND IS LIKE
WEDNESDAY NIGHT AT 8:00.
THAT'S WHAT I LOVE!
>> Jeff: MALCOLM AND CORRINE
FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> FINALLY I GOT POWER IN MY
BACK POCKET.
I GOTTEN A IDOL!
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, LAURA STRUGGLED.
LAURA WAY BACK OPENING THE DOOR
TO THE FAVORITES.
AND THE FANS LOST THEIR SECOND
CHALLENGE IN A ROW.
FAVORITES WIN IMMUNITY AND
REWARD!
FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL, LAURA
CONVINCED REYNOLD THAT THE TRIBE
WAS VOTING FOR SHAMAR AGAIN.
>> I'M ABSOLUTELY IN TO GET
SHAMAR TONIGHT.
>> THE LATEST DEVELOPMENT WHICH
I HAVE A GOOD FEELING ABOUT IS
THAT SHAMAR IS GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: BUT FOR THE SECOND
TRIBAL COUNCIL IN A ROW, SHAMAR
WAS SPARED.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR" FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES.
AND EDDIE AND REYNOLD WERE
DOOMED.
HOPE, THE TRIBE IS SPOKEN.
17 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> LET ME ASK ONE QUESTION REAL
QUICK: WHERE DO YOU THINK WE'RE
GOING TO GO FROM HERE NOW?
YOU CAN VOTE ME OUT NEXT AND
REYNOLD AFTER THAT.
>> WHERE DID YOU THINK WE WERE
GOING TO GO?
>> HE DIDN'T VOTE THE WAY YOU
WANTED TO DO IT --
>> DID YOU NOT SAY I WANT THE
STRONGEST TEAM STPHOBL.
>> YES, I SAID THAT!
YOU'RE ASKING LIKE A MAD MAN!
CALM DOWN.
>> WHY IS SHE STILL SITTING
HERE?
>> WE GOT RID OF HOPE BECAUSE
SHE WAS THE PRETTIEST WON HERE
AND SHE WAS A THREAT TO
EVERYBODY BECAUSE OF THAT.
LAURA CAN'T LIFT 20 POUNDS,
SHE'S THE WEAKEST LINK ON OUR
TEAM.
I DON'T CARE TOO MUCH FOR ANY OF
THESE PEOPLE.
>> YOU MADE ME LOOK LIKE THE
BIGGEST IDIOT EVER.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE I DIDN'T GO
ALONG WITH YOUR PLAN.
>> IT WAS YOUR PLAN!
YOU SAID PLEASE HELP ME, VOTE
FOR SHAMAR.
>> IT'S PART OF THE FREAKING
GAME!
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE ASSOCIATED
WITH YOU GUYS.
I HAVE NO RESPECT FOR ANY OF
YOU.
>> WAIT UNTIL YOU VOTE OFF ME
AND REYNOLD.
>> WE'RE NOT WINNING WITH YOU
GUYS!
>> NOW IT'S PRETTY MUCH OVER FOR
EDDIE AND I.
OUR BACKS ARE UP AGAINST THE
WALL.
I HAVE THE IMMUNITY IDOL, THAT
WILL PROTECT ME BUT EDDIE COULD
BE SCREWED.
>> AS THE SPECIALIST, ONE OF THE
THINGS YOU HAVE TO DO-- AND
NAPOLEON KNEW THIS WHEN HE WENT
TO WATERLOO-- HE COULDN'T PAY
HIS TROOPS SO HE'D GIVE THEM
NAMES AND HONOR.
IT MEANT YOU WERE A PERSON WHO
WAS LOYAL.
IN THE CASE OF BRANDON, I'VE
COME UP WITH A NAME, BUT NOT FOR
THE REASON THAT I WOULD NORMALLY
DO IT.
IT'S JUST TO GIVE HIM A SENSE
THAT HE BELONGS AND HOPEFULLY BE
ABLE TO, AS WE SAY IN THE
BUSINESS, CONTAIN THE THREAT.
I WANT TO SAY I'M VERY IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR WORK EFFORT.
YOU'VE GOT WHAT IT TAKES TO BE
OFFICIALLY A MEMBER OF STEALTH
"R" US.
>> (LAUGHS)
>> ALL THE RIGHTS AND PRIVILEGES
THEREOF.
>> OH, MY GOD, DUDE, ARE YOU
KIDDING ME?
>> YOU HAVE A NEW NAME.
YOUR STEALTH "R" US NAME IS "THE
CONQUEROR."
THAT.
>> THAT SOUNDS PRETTY BAD ASS.
>> EVERY SINGLE CHALLENGE WE'VE
PARTICIPATED IN YOU'VE
CONQUERED.
THAT'S WHY YOU GOT THAT NAME.
>> THANK YOU, BROTHER.
LET'S GET A HUG, MAN.
IT TOOK ME NINE DAYS OF KISSING
BUTT TO INFILTRATE SPECIAL AGENT
PHILLIP'S ALLIANCE.
SUPPOSEDLY PHILLIP IS SUPPOSED
TO BE ABLE TO DISCERN WHO'S
LYING TO HIM.
I'M LYING TO HIM!
THIS AGENT SUCKS BAD!
>> WELL, I'VE GIVEN YOU A NAME.
THE SILENT ONE.
PRINCIPAL RESPONSIBILITIES IS TO
COLLECT INFORMATION, SHARE IT
WITH THE APPROPRIATE PARTY.
>> GOTCHA.
>> IT KIND OF MAKES ME UPSET
THAT PHILLIP GIVES PEOPLE NOT IN
OUR ALLIANCE A NAME.
HE GAVE BRANDON A NAME.
OKAY, I LIKE THAT IDEA,
ACTUALLY.
I WISH HE WOULD HAVE CAME TO ME
FIRST BUT I LIKE THAT BRANDON
HAS A NAME.
BUT THEN PHILLIP GIVES ERIK A
NAME.
ARE WE GOING TO GIVE BRENDA A
NAME?
SERIOUSLY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS ON BEING AN
OFFICIAL MEMBER OF STEALTH "R"
US.
>> REALLY?
>> I AM KNOWN AS THE SPECIALIST.
>> (LAUGHS)
>> THERE'S TRUE GRIT.
>> THAT'S THE SILENT ONE.
>> BECAUSE I'M SILENT.
>> DOMINATRIX.
>> YOU SHOULD TAKE THAT BACK!
>> THE ELIMINATOR.
THE INTELLIGENTSIA ATTACHE.
THE ENFORCER.
THE CONQUEROR.
>> AND ME?
>> YOU ARE SERENITY.
>> NICE!
I'LL TAKE IT.
>> YOU CAN'T HAVE AN OPERATION
OF THIS MAGNITUDE UNLESS THE
SPECIALIST IS HERE IN CARAMOAN
ISLAND AND THAT'S WHY I'M HERE
TO MAKE SURE WE PULL TOGETHER AS
A COHESIVE UNIT SO WE CAN
CONTAIN THE CHALLENGE.
THAT'S THE GOAL.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE
NEW FAN TRIBE.
HOPE VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING
TO WORK.
EACH TRIBE WILL SELECT TWO TRIBE
MEMBERS TO BE PLACED ON SEPARATE
PLATFORMS.
ON MY GO, THE REST OF THE TRIBE
WILL USE PLANKS TO TRANSFER
THOSE TRIBE MEMBERS TO A THIRD
PLATFORM.
ONCE YOU'VE DONE THAT, EVERYBODY
WILL SWIM TO A FINAL VERY SMALL
PLATFORM.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO GET ALL EIGHT
MEMBERS ON OR ABOVE THE TOP OF
THE PLATFORM WIN REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: A LOCAL BUSHMAN,
SOMEBODY WHO KNOWS HOW TO LIVE
OFF THIS LAND, WILL COME TO YOUR
CAMP.
THEY'LL HAVE A HOUSE WARMING
GIFT OF A CHICKEN, FRUITS,
VEGETABLES.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: HE WILL IMPROVE EVERY
ASPECT OF YOUR LIFE.
USE HIM AS A RESOURCE.
FAVORITES, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON, SITTING SOMEBODY OUT,
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO SIT OUT
COCHRAN.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, TAKE A SPOT
ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, WE'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO!
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
FIRST YOU'VE GOT TO GET ALL
THREE OF YOUR PLANKS UNTIED.
WORKING TOGETHER VERY QUICKLY,
FANS, RIPPING THROUGH THOSE
KNOTS.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> SHAMAR HAS THE FIRST PLANK.
MICHAEL AND MATT HAVE A PLANK.
>> I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES HAVE ALL
THREE OF THEIR PLANKS.
>> RELAX.
>> Jeff: FANS HAVE ALL THREE
OF THEIR PLANKS.
THEY'RE HEADING OUT.
>> GRAB THEIR HEADS, JULIA.
>> Jeff: YOUR JOB IS TO
TRANSPORT THEM FROM ONE PLATFORM
TO THE NEXT.
>> GOOD, GOOD.
>> YOU CAN'T MOVE WITH THEM, YOU
ARE A STEP FOR THEM.
WE ARE DEAD EVEN RIGHT NOW,
JULIA MAKING NICE WORK.
BRENDAN DOING A NICE JOB.
BRENDON TO THE FIRST PLATFORM,
JULIA TO THE FIRST PLATFORM,
WE'RE DEAD EVEN RIGHT NOW.
BOTH TRIBES NOW GOING TO
TRANSPORT TWO PEOPLE, ANDREA AND
BRENDA DOING A NICE JOB.
LAURA A LITTLE SHAKY.
>> GO, GO!
GO, JULIA!
>> STAND UP!
GO FAR!
REALLY FAR!
>> Jeff: THIS TAKES A LOT OF
TEAM WORK AND COORDINATION.
>> GET CLOSER!
>> LAURA TAKING A LOT OF TIME!
FAVORITES TAKING THE LEAD!
ANDREA CROSSED FIRST FOR THE
FAVORITES.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: BRENDA ACROSS FOR THE
FAVORITES.
HEAD OUT!
EVERYBODY NOW HAS TO GET TO THAT
FINAL PLATFORM!
FANS NEED TO PICK IT UP!
LAURA'S THERE!
JULIA'S THERE!
EVERYBODY FOR THE FANS GET
ACROSS, LET'S GO!
KEEP MOVING!
>> COME ON, PHILLIP.
>> COME ON, GUY!
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE
ALL EIGHT TRIBE MEMBERS ON OR
ABOVE THE TOP OF THE PLATFORM.
>> GET ON TOP OF ME, GIRLS, I'M
FINE.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO LEAN ON EACH OTHER.
>> ARE YOU GUYS GOOD?
>> HANG ON TIGHT, GUYS, WE'RE A
ROCK.
>> Jeff: EVERY CHALLENGE THIS
SEASON HAS BEEN VERY CLOSE AND
THIS ONE IS NO DIFFERENT.
>> COME ON, GUYS, GET YOUR LEGS
UP!
>> I CAN'T GET MY FOOT UP.
>> STEP ON TOP OF MY HEAD.
>> WE HAVE TO WAIT FIVE SECONDS.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES VERY CLOSE,
THEY'RE WAITING ON CORRINE.
FANS WAITING ON MATT.
>> GET UP!
CORRINE, HURRY.
>> WE HAVE TO WAIT FIVE SECONDS!
HOLD IT!
>> PULL BACK.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES HAVE IT,
TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE.
FAVORITES WIN REWARD!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> OOH, BABY!
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT!
>> WE WON!
WE WON!
>> I DIDN'T WIN?
>> THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT!
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT!
YEAH, BABY!
>> DAMN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FAVORITES,
NICE JOB, HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO GO BACK TO CAMP.
A LOCAL BUSHMAN WILL COME TO
YOU.
THEY'LL BRING A CHICKEN, SOME
VEGGIES, SOME FRUITS.
GET BACK TO CAMP AND START
UTILIZING THAT RESOURCE.
FANS, ANOTHER CLOSE EFFORT, CAME
UP SHORT AGAIN, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> LAURA DEFINITELY SLOWED US
DOWN.
LET'S JUST VOTE HER OFF, SHE'S
WEAK, CAN WE JUST MOVE ON.
WE HAVE TO START WINNING
CHALLENGES OR WE'RE ALL SCREWED.
>> HEY!
LOOK AT OUR LITTLE GUY!
>> WHERE?
(APPLAUSE)
>> SO THE FAVORITES WON THE
REWARD CHALLENGE AND WE GOT TO
HAVE A LOCAL BUSHMAN COME TO
CAMP AND INTRODUCE US TO WAYS OF
IMPROVING OUR CAMP FOR US AS
WELL AS COOK A GREAT FEAST FOR
US.
>> WE'RE ALL REALLY EXCITED.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
NOTHING COULD HAVE PREPARED US
FOR THIS LITTLE GUY.
HIS NAME WAS TATA.
HE'S ABOUT FOUR FEET TALL, 60
YEARS OLD, HE'S ALL KNOTTED UP
WITH MUSCLE AND HE HITS THE
BEACH -- HE DOESN'T MESS AROUND.
>> LIKE A POT!
>> IT WAS ENTERTAINING MORE THAN
ANYTHING.
IT WAS JUST FUN TO WATCH HIM.
YOU COULD ONLY UNDERSTAND HALF
OF WHAT HE WAS SAYING ANYWAYS.
HE'S LIKE A FILIPINO GOLLUM.
>> OOH, VERY NICE LOAF.
VERY HOT!
OKAY, COOK RICE.
>> AS WE GOT TO FORM AS MUCH OF
A RAPPORT AS YOU CAN FORM WITH
SOMEONE LIKE TATA THE BUSHMAN,
WE GOT A SENSE OF HOW HE
FUNCTIONS AND THE WAY HE
FUNCTIONS IS SAYING ENIGMATIC
LITTLE THINGS NOBODY
UNDERSTANDS.
>> HERE IN THE JUNGLE, NO
MATCHES.
>> NO BITCHING?
NO BITCHING IN THE JUNGLE?
I LIKE THAT.
>> BUT HE CREATED AN
UNBELIEVABLE FEAST FOR US.
WE'VE BEEN EATING RICE BUT HE
PREPARED THIS RICE PHRAULESSLY
AND HE MADE CHICKEN AND POTATOES
AND ONIONS CREATED IN A WAY THAT
OSTENSIBLY WE COULD DO ONCE HE'S
GONE.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE HELL HE
WAS DOING, IT WAS GREAT TO
WATCH.
IT WAS DINNER AND A SHOW.
AND, YOU KNOW, ACTUAL HOME
IMPROVEMENT CAME ALONG WITH IT.
>> I ALMOST FELT BAD BECAUSE
THESE FANS ARE LOSING AND LOSING
AND THIS WAS A REWARD THEY COULD
HAVE USED.
IT BOOSTED THE MORALE OF OUR
TRIBE EVEN MORE.
>> OH, YEAH!
>> TATA IS A MARRIED MAN BUT
THAT DOESN'T IMPEDING HIM FROM
BUMPING AND GRINDING WITH THE
GIRLS IN THE FAVORITES TRIBE.
SINCE HE'S THIS BIZARRE LITTLE
WOODLAND CREATURE HE GETS AWAY
WITH THAT.
IF I TRIED THAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
I'M A CREEPY PREDATOR BUT THE
GIRLS FOUND IT DELIGHTFUL, THEY
WERE ALL KISSING HIM ON THE
CHEEK WHICH I'M SURE WILL
PROVIDE HIM WITH FODDER FOR
YEARS TO COME IN HIS MIND AND
HEART.
>> (LAUGHS)
WOW, WOW, OH, MY GOSH!
>> I WAS ON THE BOTTOM, I DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW WE LOST.
I THOUGHT WE WON!
>> SUCKS, MAN.
>> TODAY, YOU KNOW, WE LOST
AGAIN AND I WAS SO MAD.
THE FAVORITES HAVE EVERYTHING!
THEY'VE WON EVERY REWARD SO THEY
HAVE THIS BOUNTY OF STUFF BACK
AT THEIR CAMP.
I MEAN -- SONS OF BITCHES.
I WAS SO MAD.
I DIDN'T ANTICIPATE LOSING SO
MUCH.
>> HE JUST SITS IN THE SHELTER
ALL DAY LONG.
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
WHEN WE GOT BACK FROM THE
CHALLENGE SHAMAR WENT BACK INTO
THE SHELTER.
HE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
HE'S JUST PURE LAZINESS.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO REASON TO
BE LAYING IN THE SHELTER FOR 19
HOURS.
SHAMAR IS THE BIGGEST PAIN IN
THE ASS IN THIS TRIBE.
>> YOU WANT TO GO GET IT,
SHAMAR?
>> I'M EXHAUSTED.
CAN YOU IMAGINE BEING MY SIZE
AND HOW I FEEL?
I'M NOT LEAVING BUT Y'ALL GOING
TO BRING ME RICE ONCE A DAY.
>> ARE YOU GUYS SERIOUS?
>> (BLEEP) BE MY SLAVE AND THEN
I'LL SAY IN THE GAME.
>> IT'S NOT RIGHT.
>> THE OTHER DAY SHAMAR SAID HE
WAS GOING TO QUIT BUT HE DECIDED
TO STAY.
HOWEVER, TODAY HE SAID WELL,
HERE ARE MY TERMS.
I WILL STICK IT OUT IF I CAN LAY
HERE IN THE SHACK AND YOU GUYS
WILL SERVE ME RICE AT LEAST ONCE
A DAY.
AND I'M JUST THINKING HOW MUCH
LONGER THIS GO ON?
>> THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
CAN'T YOU JUST GET UP OFF OF
YOUR ASS AND GET YOUR OWN RICE?
>> I WOULD NEVER DO THIS IN MY
REAL LIFE.
I DON'T EVEN WAIT ON MY HUSBAND.
>> I'M SPEECHLESS.
>> WITH SHAMAR YOU CAN MAKE IT
THIS DEEP DARK STORY ABOUT THE
IRAQ VETERAN AS MUCH AS YOU WANT
BUT THAT'S NOT IT.
I THINK SHAMAR IS STARVING BUT,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'RE ALL STARVING.
SHAMAR IS A BIG BABY WHEN IT
COMES DOWN TO IT.
>> (MOANING)
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> I SCRATCHED MY EYEBALL.
>> YOU SCRATCHED YOUR EYEBALL?
>> UH-HUH.
>> THAT SUCKS.
WITH SHAMAR IT'S ALWAYS
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
NOW HE'S LAYING IN THE SHELTER
AND I GUESS A PIECE OF SAND
FALLS IN HIS EYE AND HE
SCRATCHES IT SO NOW HIS EYE
HURTS.
>> I'M DONE WITH ALL OF THE
DRAMA.
>> I KNOW.
>> IMAGINE IF WE DIDN'T HAVE
THAT DISTRACTION?
WE WOULD BE WINNING.
>> I THINK SHAMAR IS GOING TO
LOSE IT SOON.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF HE
WOUND UP QUITTING AGAIN.
>> I WAS HOPING TO PUT THIS
SHAMAR VOTE OFF FOR AS LONG AS
POSSIBLE.
>> ME, TOO.
>> NOW EVERYBODY'S GETTING
PISSED OFF AND STARTING TO
REALIZE HE HAS TO GO, WHICH IS
GREAT FOR ME AND REYNOLD.
>> LOOK AT THOSE CLOUDS.
>> DO YOU THINK IT'S GOING TO
RAIN?
>> YUP.
>> WE HAD A CRAPPY NIGHT, NEVER
FELT WINDS LIKE THAT.
RATS WERE CRAWLING ON US.
WE HAVE CUTS AND SCRAPES AND
BRUISES, WE'RE HUNGRY.
IT'S A HARD GAME AND NOW IT'S
EVEN HARDER BECAUSE WE BELIEVE
THAT SHAMAR IS GOING TO QUIT.
SHAMAR IS SITTING THERE ROCKING
BACK AND FORTH.
I THINK HE'S MEDICATING.
IT'S LIKE HE CAN'T GET TO A
HAPPY PLACE.
I'M LIKE WHO CAN AROUND HERE,
YOU KNOW?
>> THE FRIGGING GUY DOESN'T WANT
TO BE HERE.
>> HIS EYE IS PUFFY.
>> I'M SORRY, MAN, EVERYONE'S
DINGED UP.
YOU'RE A (BLEEP)ING MARINE, COME
ON!
>> YESTERDAY A PIECE OF SAND GOT
IN MY EYE AND I GUESS I
SCRATCHED MY EYE.
IT GOT SWOLLEN AND I COULDN'T
SLEEP AT NIGHT.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT IT.
I'M NOT THINKING ABOUT THE GAME,
I JUST KIND OF WANT MY EYE FIXED
A LITTLE BIT.
>> HERE COMES JEFF, GUYS.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, YOU DON'T
LOOK SO GOOD.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH MY
EYE.
>> Jeff: WOW, IT'S REALLY
SWOLLEN.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE GOT MEDICAL
HERE, ALL RIGHT?
THEY'RE GOING TO GIVE YOU AN
ASSESSMENT AND SEE HOW IT'S
DOING.
>> SHAMAR, THE FIRST THING I'M
GOING TO DO IS TRY TO HAVE A
LOOK INSIDE YOUR EYE BUT WE'LL
DO IT SLOWLY.
YOU JUST TALK TO ME.
SO THE WHOLE EYE JUST LOOKS VERY
RED AT THE MOMENT, SHAMAR.
I KNOW THAT'S UNCOMFORTABLE.
I'M GOING TO CLOSE IT AGAIN.
WHAT I NEED TO RULE OUT IS THAT
HE HADN'T GOTTEN A ABRASION OR
ABNORMALITY ON HIS CORNEA WHICH
IS THE CLEAR PART THAT COVERS
HIS EYE THE ONLY WAY TO DO THAT
IS PUT IN AN ORANGE DYE AND I'M
ABLE TO SEE THING MRS. CLEARLY.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
>> Jeff: THIS HAS BEEN AN
EVENTFUL JOURNEY FOR YOU.
YOU'VE HAD SOME LOWS WHERE
PEOPLE HAVE ATTACKED YOU YOU'VE
HAD SOME HIGHS, YOU'VE BEEN ONE
OF THE BIGGEST CHEERLEADERS ON
THIS TRIBE.
>> I FOUGHT HARD AND DID MY BEST
BUT IT'S A LOT OF PAIN RIGHT
NOW.
>> THERE'S ACTUALLY TWO THERE.
>> IT ACTUALLY LOOKS LIKE THERE
IS WHAT I WOULD CALL A DIVOT IN
HIS CORNEA.
IT'S RIGHT NEXT TO HIS PUPIL OR
ON THE COLORED PART OF HIS EYE.
IT COULD AFFECT HIS VISION.
>> THAT'S A BIG CONCERN.
IS THERE SOMETHING WE CAN DO OUT
HERE?
>> UNFORTUNATELY NOT.
I THINK FROM MY PERSPECTIVE I
WOULD LIKE TO PULL YOU FROM THE
GAME TO HAVE THIS LOOKED INTO BY
A SPECIALIST.
>> Jeff: HOW'S THAT LANDING
WITH YOU, SHAMAR?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
>> Jeff: DO YOU FEEL IN SOME
WAY EVEN THOUGH IT'S NOT YOUR
FAULT THAT YOU'RE LETTING YOUR
TRIBE DOWN?
BECAUSE THEY'RE LOSING NOT ONLY
A BIG FORCE IN CHALLENGES BUT A
NUMBER IN A GAME ABOUT NUMBERS.
>> I KNOW.
I MEAN, I WOULD NEVER WANT TO
LEAVE THE GAME LIKE THIS.
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE MY VISION.
I DON'T WANT TO RISK IT.
>> Jeff: DO YOU WANT MANY TOE
BRING THE TRIBE IN SO YOU CAN
SAY GOOD-BYE?
>> YEAH.
>> HEY, GUYS, COME ON IN.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN UPDATE.
WE'VE JUST HAD OUR DOCTORS CHECK
HIM OUT.
THEY GAVE HIM A THOROUGH
ASSESSMENT AND HIS EYE IS IN
PRETTY ROUGH SHAPE.
HE'S GOT TO BE TAKEN OUT OF THE
GAME.
>> SORRY, SHAMAR.
>> I HOPE YOU HEAL QUICKLY.
>> THANK YOU, I APPRECIATE YOU
GUYS, I DO.
I KNOW THAT YOU CARE ABOUT MY
WELL-BEING AND I REALLY HOPE YOU
GUYS DO WELL, HONESTLY.
>> Jeff: SHAMAR, LET'S GET YOU
OUT OF HERE, WE'LL GET YOU ON A
BOAT TO SEE A SPECIALIST.
FOR YOU GUYS, YOU'LL GATHER YOUR
STUFF AND I'LL SEE YOU AT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE THIS MORNING.
LET'S GET HIM UP.
>> I WAS IN THE MARINE CORPS
FOUR YEARS, I DID TWO TOURS IN
IRAQ AND NEVER GOT HURT.
THE PEOPLE WHO KNOW ME KNOW THAT
I'M A STRONG GUY AND THAT IT
TAKES A LOT TO BRING ME DOWN.
"SURVIVOR" IS A TOUGH GAME.
THANK YOU, I APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF SHAMAR,
MAN.
WHEN SHAMAR WAS CLAIMING HIS EYE
WAS SCRATCH SOD BAD I WAS
THINKING HE EMOTIONALLY DIDN'T
WANT TO PLAY ANYMORE.
IT TURNS OUT IT WAS VERY SERIOUS
SO THAT'S MY MISTAKE.
STILL, HE WAS DISRESPECTFUL,
LAZY AND I'M JUST HAPPY HE'S
GONE.
>> GLAD IT'S OVER.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT YOU DO SEE, LIKE, ONE OF
THEM GOING BEFORE ONE OF US?
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE ALL GOOD.
THERE'S NOTHING THAT CAN HAPPEN.
>> HOWEVER, NOW THAT SHAMAR IS
GONE THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE ARE
GOING TO JUMP BACK INTO THEIR
PREMEDITATED PLAN AND KNOCK OFF
EDDIE AND I FIRST.
SO WE HAVE TO WIN OR ONE OF US
IS GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
FAVORITES GETTING YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW TRIBE OF FANS.
>> WAIT, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> SHAMAR IS NO LONGER IN THIS
GAME DUE TO A SEVERE EYE INJURY
THAT NEEDED IMMEDIATE ATTENTION.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: TRIBE OF FANS NOW
DOWN TO SEVEN.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THING'S FIRST,
BRANDON, GOING TO TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO SWIM OUT TO A PLATFORM,
CLIMB TO THE TOP, SMASH A TILE,
RETRIEVE A KEY AND SWIM BACK,
THEN THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE RETRIEVED FIVE KEYS
THE TWO REMAINING TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL USE THOSE KEYS TO OPEN A
CHEST.
YOU WILL USE THE SANDBAGS INSIDE
TO KNOCK OFF ALL THE BLOCKS FROM
YOUR LEDGE DROPPING YOUR TRIBE'S
FLAG.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, AVOIDS TRIBAL COUNCIL,
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT OF YOUR TRIBE.
FAVORITES, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
MEMBERS, SITTING TWO PEOPLE OUT,
CANNOT SIT OUT THE SAME PEOPLE.
COCHRAN SAT OUT THE LAST
CHALLENGE.
WHO'S IT GOING SNOB.
>> CORRINE AND DAWN.
>>
>> Jeff: CORRINE AND DAWN TAKE
A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND GET STARTED.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GO -R, SHERRI.
>> Jeff: SHERRI TAKES A BIG
FALL, ERIK DOES, TOO.
SHERRI CALLING ACROSS, ERIK
CRAWLING ACROSS.
ERIK ACROSS FOR THE FAVORITES.
>> YOU'RE LEADING, ERIK.
>> Jeff: SHERRI THERE FOR THE
FANS.
>> ERIK, YOU GOT THIS!
>> Jeff: ERIK TO THE PLATFORM
FIRST.
FAVORITES OUT TO AN EARLY LEAD.
>> COME ON, ERIK, YOU'VE DONE
THIS.
>> Jeff: ERIK HAS NO PROBLEM!
ERIK NOW HAS THE FIRST KEY, HE'S
HEADING BACK.
SHERR I CLIPS THE EDGE BUT
DOESN'T RELEASE THE KEY.
YOU HAVE TO GO BACK UP.
THE TRIBE ALREADY DOWN ON THEIR
LUCK IS OFF TO A SLOW START IN
THIS IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> GOOD BOY, ERIK!
>> Jeff: ERIK IS BACK WITH THE
FIRST KEY.
BRANDON ATTACKING THESE
PLATFORMS VERY FAST!
SHERRI HAS THE FIRST KEY FOR THE
FANS.
>> BRANDON, YOU GOT THIS!
>> Jeff: BRANDON CONNECTS, HE
HAS THE SECOND KEY.
>> WAY TO GO, BRANDON!
>> Jeff: SHERRI COMPLETELY
SPENT.
MATT NOW IN THE WATER FOR THE
FANS.
BRANDON IS BACK, BRENDA IS NOW
IN THE WATER FOR THE FAVORITES.
BRENDA WITH A VER HARD FALL.
MATT HAS THE SECOND KEY.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
BRENDA'S NOT MESSING AROUND AT
ALL!
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
FAVORITES HAVE A ONE-KEY
ADVANTAGE WHICH IS HUGE.
BRENDA VERY CLOSE TO LAPPING
MATT.
ANDREA IN THE WATER.
EDDIE IN THE WATER.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO IT, EDDIE!
>> LOW TO THE GROUND!
>> Jeff: EDDIE KNOWS HE'S GOT
TO MAKE UP SOME TIME.
>> RIGHT DOWN THE MIDDLE!
RIGHT DOWN THE PIKE.
>> Jeff: THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
EDDIE HAS THE THIRD KEY FOR THE
FANS.
HE'S GOT TO GET BACK QUICKLY!
>> LET'S GO AN ANDREA.
>> Jeff: AND SHE GETS IT WITH
A NICE SMASH.
ANDREA HAS THE FOURTH KEY FOR
THE FAVORITES.
EDDIE'S BACK WITH THE THIRD KEY.
JULIA NOW OUT ON THE COURSE.
ANDREA'S BACK, MALCOLM HEADING
OUT FOR THAT FIFTH AND FINAL
KEY.
TAKES A BIG HIT BUT NOT
DETERRED.
JULIA GOING FOR THAT FOURTH KEY.
AND SHE DOES, JUST BARELY.
JULIA HAS THE FOURTH KEY.
MALCOLM NO PROBLEM GETTING THAT
FIFTH KEY FOR THE FAVORITES.
FAVORITES HAVE ALL FIVE KEYS.
MICHAEL STILL GOT TO GO.
HE HAS A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE UP.
MALCOLM BACK WITH THE FIFTH AND
FINAL KEY.
START WORKING ON YOUR LOCKS.
>> IF IT DOESN'T GO IN TRY THE
NEXT ONE.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP AND COCHRAN
WORKING ON THE LOCKS FOR THE
FAVORITES.
THERE ARE FIVE KEYS, THERE ARE
THREE LOCKS.
>> LET'S GO, GUYS.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES HAVE ONE
LOCK UNDONE.
MICHAEL TO THE TOP, HE'S GOT TO
CONNECT RIGHT HERE HE'S GOT IT!
MICHAEL'S GOT TO SWIM BACK
QUICKLY NOW.
>> MICHAEL, WE'RE STILL IN THIS!
>> GOT THIS ONE.
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP HAS THE
SECOND LOCK UNDONE FOR THE
FAVORITES.
>> GOT IT.
>> Jeff: FAVORITES HAVE THEIR
THIRD LOCK UNDONE.
>> BRING THIS HOME!
COME ON.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP STARTS
THROWING FOR THE FAVORITES.
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: THERE YOU, GO FANS
HAVE ALL FIVE KEYS.
REYNOLD AND LAURA START WORKING
ON THOSE LOCKS.
YOU NEED TO MOVE QUICKLY, FANS.
ONE LOCK OFF.
>> NICE!
>> WHERE THE (BLEEP) OH!
>> Jeff: LAURA HAVING A TOUGH
TIME WITH THE LOCKS.
>> YEAH, PHILLIP!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES HAVE A HUGE
LEAD.
SECOND LOCK OFF.
FANS DOWN TO ONE LOCK LEFT.
FANS HAVE THEIR THIRD LOCK.
>> MAGIC TIME, BABY.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD STARTS
TOSSING HE HAS A LOT OF GROUND
TO MAKE UP.
>> SPECIALIST, YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: PHILLIP KNOCKS OFF
MORE BLOCKS.
REYNOLD KNOCKS OFF SEVERAL
BLOCKS.
AND ANOTHER THREE.
HE'S ON A ROLL.
AND ANOTHER TWO!
PHILLIP KNOCKS OFF TWO MORE!
PHILLIP DOWN TO FOUR BLOCKS
LEFT.
REYNOLD HAS MADE UP A LOT OF
GROUND.
REYNOLD KNOCKS OFF TWO MORE.
FANS ARE CATCHING UP!
IT'S A HUGE COMEBACK!
ANOTHER ONE FOR REYNOLD.
PHILLIP'S STARTING TO GET
EXHAUSTED.
PHILLIP KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER ONE!
>> TWO MORE!
TWO MORE!
>> Jeff: REYNOLD NEEDS TO PICK
IT UP!
REYNOLD KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER ONE.
FAVORITES ARE DOWN TO TWO.
PHILLIP KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER ONE!
FAVORITES HAVE ONE LEFT.
FANS HAVE SIX.
PHILLIP COULD WIN IMMUNITY FOR
THE TPA +EUFRTSS RIGHT HERE.
OH!
SHORT!
FANS ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
ANOTHER SHOT FOR PHILLIP TO WIN
IT.
(SCREAMING)
HE DOES!
PHILLIP WINS IMMUNITY FOR THE
FAVORITES.
>> GREAT JOB!
>> DAMN IT.
>> YOU ARE THE SPECIALIST!
YOU ARE!
>> Jeff: FAVORITES, IT'S
COMING BACK ONCE AGAIN.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR THE
FAVORITES.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
FANS, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK
TO CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
SO LIKE, IT
TOOK ME A MINUTE TO KIND OF GET
MY BEARINGS WITH THEM.
>> TO CATCH UP AS MUCH AS WE
DID, IT'S AMAZING.
BUT THE FACT THAT WE ARE GOING
TO LOSE TWO PEOPLE IN ONE DAY
REALLY --
>> SUCKS.
>> --BAD.
>> WELL, WE LOST AGAIN SO WE'RE
GOING BACK TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ME AND REYNOLD ARE STILL ON THE
VERY OUTSIDE OF THIS TRIBE.
I HAVE A HUGE TARGET ON MY BACK.
REYNOLD FEELS THE SAME WAY AND
IF WE DON'T FIGURE OUT A NEW
PLAN ONE OF US IS GOING HOME.
>> I'M GOING TO WALK DOWN THIS
TRIAL.
>> YEAH, IT'S EXACTLY AS I
SUPPOSED.
THEY'RE ALREADY BUSY, BUSY, BUSY
OVER THERE.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO BLIND
SIDE ME BECAUSE I HAVE AN IDOL.
>> SO YOU MEAN ME?
>> IT COULD BE YOU.
>> IT IS ME.
>> WE'RE NOT DEAD YET.
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY SAY.
>> HERE'S MY THING, DUDE, ME,
YOU, REYNOLD AND EDDIE ARE THE
ONLY REASON WHY WE ARE CLOSE IN
THAT CHALLENGE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> SO, I MEAN, AS MUCH AS I HATE
TO SAY IT, THE SMARTEST THING
WOULD BE TO BE TO VOTE OUT
LAURA.
I MEAN, THE THING IS, MICHAEL,
IT'S LIKE, IT'S TOUGH AND IT
SUCKS BUT WE HAVE TO WIN
CHALLENGES AND EDDIE AND REYNOLD
ARE OUR TWO STRONGEST PEOPLE.
>> I JUST ASSUMED EVERYONE WAS
GOING TO TRY AND GET REYNOLD TO
PLAY THE IDOL AND VOTE OUT EDDIE
BUT ALL OF A SUDDEN MATT IS LIKE
"WE NEED TO KEEP THE TRIBE
STRONG AND GET RID OF LAURA."
AND I'M LIKE THERE GOES THE
ALLIANCE.
>> I SEE LAURA GETTING BEAT DOWN
AND KIND OF --
>> SHE HAS THAT 500 YARD STARE.
SHE'S VERY WEAK.
>> IT'S A BUMMER BUT I THINK
IT'S OUR BEST MOVE, DUDE.
>> I KNEW AS SOON AS THE
ALLIANCE WAS FORMED THAT IT
WASN'T THE ALLIANCE OF THE
STRONG PEOPLE.
BUT I TRUST LAURA MORE THAN I
TRUST REYNOLD AND EDDIE SO IT
COULD BE DANGEROUS TO LOSE HER
AND LEAVE, YOU KNOW, THIS WILD
CARD MR. AWESOME WITH THE IDOL.
>> MICHAEL AND I WANT TO VOTE
LAURA.
SHE'S THE WEAKEST LINK, IF IT
WASN'T FOR THE FOUR GUYS WE
WOULD HAVE WON THE CHALLENGE.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TELLING YOU --
>> YOU GUYS COULD BE SETTING US
UP AGAIN SO WE DON'T DO ANY IDOL
PLAYING.
>> HERE'S THE THING, DUDE, THE
REASON WE CAME CLOSE IN MOST OF
THE CHALLENGES IS BECAUSE OF
YOU.
I'M NOT A DUMB ASS.
LAURA WAS BREATHING HEAVY AFTER
TRYING TO UNLOCK LOCKS.
>> MATT AAPPROACHED ME AND HE
SAID HE WANTS TO GET THE MUSCLE
BACK TOGETHER AND TRY AND WIN
CHALLENGES.
WELL, LA DEDA.
HE'S BOLDFACED LIED TO ME ON
MORE OCCASIONS THAN I CAN COUNT.
YOU GUYS HAVE PUT ME ON THE
ROPES SINCE DAY TWO.
>> THE WAY I LOOK AT IT, DUDE,
IS IF YOU FEEL THREATENED PLAY
YOUR IDOL.
I AM GOING TO VOTE LAURA.
>> I SHOULD PROBABLY PLAY THE
IDOL TONIGHT AND JUST SAVE
MYSELF, HOWEVER, IF THEY DO VOTE
LAURA AND I PLAY THE IDOL IT'S
IDOL WASTED.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO.
>> EVERYBODY'S TALKING.
>> WE MIGHT HAVE TO SPLIT THE
VOTE AGAIN.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AT THIS POINT, I'M PRETTY
SURE REYNOLD AND EDDIE ARE
THROWING MY NAME AROUND AND THAT
MAKES ME VERY NERVOUS.
BECAUSE THEY KNOW AT THIS POINT
THAT MY TRIBE DOESN'T HAVE A LOT
OF CONFIDENCE IN ME IN
CHALLENGES.
SO I'M DEFINITELY WORRIED.
THE ONLY THING I CAN DO AT THIS
POINT IS TRUST IN MY ALLIANCE
AND HOPE IT ALL SWINGS MY WAY.
>> MY MAIN CONCERN RIGHT NOW IS
WE HAVE TO WIN CHALLENGES SO I
SAY WE GET RID OF OUR WEAKEST
LING, WHICH IS LAURA, AND THAT'S
WHAT I'M THINKING.
>> YOU DON'T THINK IT'S
DANGEROUS KEEPING REYNOLD AND --
>> HERE'S THE DEAL, IF IT WASN'T
FOR THOSE TWO GUYS WE WOULDN'T
WIN ANY CHALLENGES.
>> WE HAVEN'T WON ANY CHALLENGES
YET.
>> WE DID WIN ONE AND IT WAS
BECAUSE REYNOLD WAS A BAD ASS.
>> WHEN LAURA'S NAME GOT BROUGHT
UP I WAS NOT ON BOARD WITH IT AT
ALL.
FIRST WE LOST SHAMAR, NOW THIS.
IT FEELS LIKE THE ALLIANCE IS
FALLING APART.
ALSO, IF THEY KEEP SAYING
THEY'RE PICKING OFF THE WEAK AND
NEED TO KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG,
WELL, OF COURSE THE GUYS ARE
GOING TO BE ALWAYS STRONGER THAN
THE WOMEN.
SO OF COURSE THAT CONCERNS ME.
MATT THINKS WE NEED TO VOTE
LAURA OUT.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT US
BEING THE LAST TWO GIRLS.
THEY KEEP TALKING ABOUT STUFF.
>> ARE YOU STILL WITH OUR FIVE
RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW YOU GUYS ARE CONCERNED
WITH THAT IDOL.
I MEAN, IT COULD BE AS SIMPLE AS
BOYS EDDIE, GIRLS REYNOLD OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> THAT MAKES SENSE TO ME.
>> TONIGHT I HAVE TO EITHER KEEP
THE TRIBE STRONG SO THAT WE CAN
WIN CHALLENGES OR HOLD ON TO MY
ALLIANCE AND KEEP THAT STRONG
AND THERE'S NO WAY TO KNOW WHAT
THE RIGHT OR WRONG ANSWER IS
GOING TO BE.
SO JUST GOING TO HAVE TO GO WITH
MY GUT AND HOPE IT WORKS OUT.
>> Jeff: SO, MATT, TELL ME
ABOUT THIS TRIBE NOW THAT SHAMAR
IS GONE.
HOW DOES THIS HURT THE TRIBE OR
HOW DOES IT HELP THE TRIBE?
>> YOU KNOW, NOW THAT SHAMAR IS
GONE I THINK THERE'S LESS
TENSION AROUND CAMP HOWEVER WE
LOST A BIG GUY GOOD TO HELPOUS
OUT IN CHALLENGES AND IT'S OUR
THIRD TRIBAL IN THE ROW SO IT
SUCKS TO HAVE SHAMAR GONE.
>> Jeff: SHERRI, DO YOU MISS
SHAMAR OR IS IT A BIT OF A
RELIEF?
>> I WOULD SAY I MISS SHAMAR AS
FAR AS PART OF THE ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: WOW, A VERY SLOW
THOUGHTFUL ANSWER.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, WHERE IS
THIS TRIBE NOW?
>> I OBVIOUSLY HAVE VOTED
AGAINST THE TRIBE THE FIRST TWO
TRIBAL COUNCILS.
I THOUGHT GETTING SHAMAR OUT
FIRST WE COULD HAVE STARTED TO
GEL BUT THERE'S A STRONG
ALLIANCE OF FIVE HERE AND
THEY'RE VERY HESITANT TO BREAK
IT UP.
YET WITHOUT EDDIE AND I YOUR
CHANCES OF WINNING ANY MORE
CHALLENGES ARE VERY SLIM.
>> Jeff: LAURA, REYNOLD MAKES
A GOOD ARGUMENT.
THE TWO GUYS ON THE OUTSIDE OF
THE ALLIANCE ARE TWO OF THE
STRONGEST GUYS IN THE
CHALLENGES.
>> SURE, BUT, YOU KNOW,
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL IS DEFINITELY
BASED ON WHETHER WE'RE GOING TO
PRIORITIZE PHYSICAL STRENGTH OR
OUR LOYALTIES AND OUR ALLIANCES
AND WHICH ONE OF THOSE TWO IS
GOING TO GET US FURTHER IN THIS
GAME.
>> Jeff: AND WHAT'S YOUR CASE?
IF YOU HEARD SOMEBODY WHISPERING
SAYING "LAURA KILLED US AGAIN,
LET'S VOTE LAURA OUT --".
>> THE PHYSICAL STRENGTH VOTES
TEND TO HAPPEN VERY EARLY ON IN
THE GAME BEFORE RELATIONSHIPS
ARE FORMED.
WE HAVE HAD TEN DAYS TO BUILD
TRUST AND THAT'S HUGE AT THIS
POINT IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: REYNOLD, YOU'RE
SHAKING YOUR HEAD.
>> YEAH, IN LISTENING TO ALL OF
THIS I CAN'T WRAP MY HEAD AROUND
IT.
THEY'RE ALL ABOUT TRUST TO EACH
OTHER BUT WE'RE LOSING, LOSING,
LOSING.
ARE YOU PRIORITIZING WINNING OR
ARE YOU PRIORITIZING LOSING?
>> Jeff: SHERRI, REYNOLD TODAY
ALMOST SINGLE-HANDEDLY BROUGHT
YOU GUYS BACK.
>> BUT WE'RE STILL LOSING.
EVEN WITH THEM.
WE'RE STILL LOSING.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE SAYING
KEEPING REYNOLD, KEEPING EDDIE,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN IT'S GOING TO
CHANGE ANYTHING, ALL IT WILL DO
IS BREAK OUR ALLIANCE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> Jeff: EDDIE, YOU'VE BEEN ON
THE BOTTOM FROM THE GET-GO.
>> YEAH.
IN THAT ASPECT, ME AND REYNOLD
ARE FIGHTING WITH OUR BACKS
AGAINST THE WALL.
IF WE COME TOGETHER NOW AND GET
RID OF OUR WEAKEST PLAYER AND GO
FORWARD AND START WINNING WE
DON'T HAVE TO COME BACK HERE.
>> Jeff: WOULD YOU PUT CHERNY
THE CATEGORY OF ONE OF THE
WEAKER PLAYERS?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: HOW ABOUT JULIA?
>> JULIA IS ONE OF THE STRONGER
GIRLS SINCE WE'VE BEEN HERE.
>> Jeff: HOW ABOUT LAURA?
>> LAURA UNFORTUNATELY IS THE
WEAKEST PLAYER WE HAVE ON OUR
TEAM.
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: HARD TO HEAR, LAURA?
>> IT IS HARD TO HEAR, BUT WE
ALL KNOW THIS GAME PRETTY WELL.
THERE ARE CERTAIN TWISTS TO IT
AND IF NUMBERS WERE JUMBLED OVER
THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS AND WE
ALL ENDED UP ON DIFFERENT TRIBES
IT'S LIKE PREDICTING THE FUTURE.
ARE EDDIE AND REYNOLD GOING TO
BE AS LOYAL AS OUR ALLIANCE
RIGHT NOW?
OR ARE THEY GOING TO BE MORE
WILLING TO JUMP SHIP?
>> Jeff: SO EDDIE, REALLY, THE
THIRD FACTOR IN THIS, LOYALTY
VERSUS STRENGTH, IS PREDICTING
THE FUTURE.
>> I MEAN, LAST TWO TRIBAL
COUNCILS I WAS TOLD EVERYBODY
WAS VOTING FOR SHAMAR AND I
VOTED FOR SHAMAR TWICE SO IF I'M
STILL HERE IN 20 MINUTES I'M
GOING TO FEEL A LOT DIFFERENTLY
ABOUT THIS TRIBE THAN I DO RIGHT
NOW, TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I THINK TONIGHT IS THE MAKE OR
BREAK FACTOR FOR THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S FIND
OUT IF IT IS, INDEED, MAKE OR
BREAK.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JULIA, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU'RE THE WEAKEST LINK IN
THE TEAM AND IT'S KILL OR BE
KILLED.
>> TOO DANGEROUS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
>> GOT TO DO IT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
THIS IS THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR REYNOLD WILL
NOT COUNT.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL, PERSON VOTED
OUT WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELIMENT I'LL READ THE
VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LAURA.
LAURA.
REYNOLD.
DOES NOT COUNT.
LAURA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES LAURA.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: FANS VERSUS
FAVORITES."
LAURA, THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S
ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU BROKE FORM
TONIGHT AND VOTED SOMEBODY FROM
THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE OUT OF
THIS GAME.
MAYBE IT WAS A MAKE-OR-BREAK
VOTE.
TIME WILL TELL.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR" -- EVERY SEASON THERE
IS ONE MOMENT --
>> I'M THE AUTHOR OF MY FATE,
BUDDY!
>> Jeff: THAT NO ONE WILL EVER
FORGET.
>> WHERE IS IT?
GO!
NO!
>> NO!
(BLEEP) COME ON!
NOW VOTE ME OUT, BITCH!
>> AS A VIEWER FROM THE COUCH,
YOU REALLY ONLY GET TO SEE ONE
SIDE, YOU DON'T FEEL THE HUNGER,
YOU DON'T FEEL THE THIRST IN
YOUR MOUTH.
IT'S VERY REAL.
I KNEW COMING IN HERE THAT MY
MUSCLES WEREN'T MY BIGGEST ASSET
AND I USED EVERYTHING ELSE I
HAD.
I THINK A LOT OF MY PLANS WERE
LEFT UNRESOLVED BUT GOOD LUCK TO
THE REST OF THEM.
THEY REALLY GOT ME.