>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR."
AFTER 26 DAYS, TWO THINGS WERE
CERTAIN.
KATIE WAS ALONE AT THE BOTTOM.
>> I'M NOW SO LOAN IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: AND CIERA AND LAURA
WERE THE LAST PAIR IN THIS GAME.
>> DID YOU THINK WE'D BE THE
LAST COUPLE?
>> Jeff: BUT CIERA'S ALLIANCE,
THE TADHANA 5, CAME UP WITH A
PLAN TO BREAK UP HER AND HER
MOM.
>> I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING AND YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BE SUPER HAPPY.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO VOTE MY MOM.
>> Jeff: FORTUNATELY FOR THEM,
SEE CARE A WAS ON BOARD.
>> IF MY MOM NEEDS TO GO IN
ORDER FOR ME TO WIN THE GAME,
THAT'S SOMETHING TO LOOK AT.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: BUT THE PRESSURE OF
VOTING OUT HER MOM WAS TAKING
ITS TOLL.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
TO VOTE MY MOM OUT.
I CAME INTO THIS, LIKE, WANTING
TO SPLIT THE END WITH MY MOM,
BUT --
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
CIERA MADE THE TOUGHEST AND MOST
EMOTIONAL VOTE OF THE SEASON.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. WATER,"
VOTING OUT OTHER MOM.
SENDING HER BACK TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SEVEN ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE
VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> SORRY I CRIED.
>> LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE INCLUDED
CIERA VOTED FOR HER MOM.
SO I'M SURPRISED THAT CIERA
CHOSE WATER OVER BLOOD.
BUT SYRIA A HAS A PLAN AND I
DON'T THINK HER MOM WAS PART OF
IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW, LIKE, I'M
WEIRDLY OKAY WITH IT.
I KNEW THAT IT WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN EVENTUALLY.
TONIGHT WAS REALLY ROUGH.
IT WAS NOT EASY HAVING TO WRITE
MY MOM'S NAME DOWN BUT I'VE
PROVEN 100% THAT I'M TRUSTWORTHY
IN MOVING FORWARD.
I HOPE PEOPLE TAKE ME SERIOUSLY
IN THE GAME AND WANT TO WORK
WITH ME.
>> CIERA, I PRAERB@WHAT YOU DID
TONIGHT.
I KNOW NOBODY HAD TO PUT A VOTE
DOWN THAT WAS AS HARD AS IT WAS
FOR YOU.
CIERA WRITING HER MOM'S NAME
DOWN IT WAS HARDEST VOTING
POSITION OF THE GAME SO FAR.
BY DOING THAT, SHE'S SHOWING
LOYALTY.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, IT MAKES
ME SCARED OF HER.
I CAN SEE SHE'S PLAYING THE GAME
PRETTY HARD.
I THINK SHE'S UNDERESTIMATED BY
A LOT OF PEOPLE AND WILL BE
DANGEROUS.
>> SO FUNNY, I'M BOTH NERVOUS
AND EXCITED.
NERVOUS THAT IT'S KATIE BUT I'M
ALSO EXCITED IF IT'S KATIE.
>> MOM?
>> KATIE?
OH!
HONEY!
>> OH!
>> OTHER MOM.
>> IT'S NOT KATIE!
>> I HEAR A LITTLE VOICE GOING
"MOM?"
AND I'M LIKE, OH, IT'S KATIE!
BUT NO, IT WAS LAURA M.
BACK ONCE AGAIN TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
>> CIERA TOOK ME TO THE BEACH
AND SAID "MOM, THEY'RE GOING TO
VOTE YOU OUT UNLESS YOU CAN DO
SOMETHING."
AND THEN SHE HAD TO PUT MY NAME
DOWN.
>> WOW.
>> I'M HAVING A HARD TIME
DEFINING HOW I'M FEELING ABOUT
CIERA WRITING MY NAME DOWN
BECAUSE IT SUCKS THAT I'M HERE,
IT SUCKS THAT CIERA HAD TO DO
THAT.
IT SUCKS THAT SHE DID THAT.
BUT I'M PROUD OF HER.
I MEAN, SHE'S PLAYING THE GAME.
>> IT WAS JUST TOUGH.
IT WAS REALLY TOUGH.
WE WERE THE ONLY ONE LOVED ONE
COUPLES AND THEY WERE THREATENED
BY ME STILL.
WHICH THEY'RE STUPID, MONICA'S
WINNING THE CHALLENGES AND TYSON
IS FLYING UNDER THE RADAR.
>> TYSON IS SO -- HE'S RUNNING
IT!
WHY ISN'T ANYBODY VOTING HIM
OUT?
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
VYTAS, TINA AND LAURA VOTED OUT
FOR THE SECOND TIME AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, LAURA, THE LAST VOTE WE
SHOWED AT TRIBAL SAID "MOM."
CIERA VOTED YOU OUT OF THIS
GAME.
SHE VOTED HER MOM OUT.
>> I'M PROUD OF HER.
WE KNEW AT SOME POINT ONE OF US
WOULD HAVE TO VOTE THE OTHER ONE
OUT.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK IT WAS GOING
TO BE SO SOON, AND IT'S OKAY.
>> SORRY!
>> IT'S OKAY.
I'LL COME BACK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAURA, IF
YOU WANT BACK IN THIS GAME,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE
SURE YOU FINISH BEFORE EITHER
TINA OR VYTAS.
TWO PEOPLE WILL MOVE ON, ONE
WON'T.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU'RE GOING
TO RACE TO REMOVE FOUR COLORED
CUBES FROM A LONG NET TUNNEL.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL FOUR YOU MUST
STACK THEM SO THERE ARE NO
REPEATING COLORS ON ANY SIDE.
FIRST TWO TO FINISH LIVE TO SEE
DAY 28 IN THIS GAME.
THE LOSER IS OUT FOR GOOD AND
WILL JOIN ARAS ON THE JURY AS
THE SECOND MEMBER.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER OF THIS
DUEL DECIDES WHO GETS THE CLUE
TO THE LOCATION OF THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT IS BECOMING A BIGGER AND
BIGGER STORY EVERY SINGLE DAY.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
TWO WILL MOVE ON.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> LET'S GO, GUYS.
>> Jeff: THAT ROPE IS ROUGH.
IT'S GOING TO BEAT UP YOUR HANDS
BUT YOU CAN'T WORRY ABOUT THAT
RIGHT NOW.
VYTAS HAS HIS FIRST BOX.
LAURA HAS HER FIRST BOX.
IT'S VYTAS AND LAURA OUT TO A
QUICK START.
TINA HAS HER FIRST ONE.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: VYTAS MAKING QUICK
WORK OF THIS.
VYTAS HAS HIS SECOND BOX.
THERE ARE FOUR TOTAL.
LAURA HAS HER SECOND BOX.
>> GOOD JOB, MOM.
>> Jeff: TINA REALLY SLOWING
DOWN.
>> POP IT HARD, MOM!
>> Jeff: IT'S VYTAS AND LAURA
BOTH WORKING ON THEIR THIRD.
VYTAS HAS HIS THIRD.
LAURA HAS HER THIRD.
TINA HAS HER SECOND.
SHE'S ONE FULL BOX BEHIND.
THAT IS A LOT OF TIME.
>> THERE YOU GO, MOM, BE QUICK.
>> Jeff: VYTAS ALMOST ROLLING
HIS THROUGH NOW.
LAURA HAS A GOOD RHYTHM.
RIGHT NOW IT'S TINA THAT'S IN
TROUBLE.
VYTAS VERY CLOSE.
VYTAS HAS HIS FOURTH!
HE CAN START SOLVING IT.
LAURA HAS HER FOURTH AND SHE IS
WORKING ON HER PUZZLE NOW.
TINA STILL WORKING ON HER THIRD.
WHAT YOU ARE TRYING TO DO NOW IS
ASSEMBLE THIS SO THAT THERE ARE
NO REPEATING COLORS ON ANY
SIDEN'T.
>> OH, THERE WE GO!
>> Jeff: TINA HAS HER THIRD,
NOW WORKING ON HER FOURTH.
MEANWHILE, LAURA AND VYTAS HAVE
BEEN WORKING ON THIS PUZZLE
ALREADY.
THIS IS LAURA'S SECOND SHOT AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND ARENA.
CAN SHE LIVE TO SEE DAY 28 AND A
SHOT TO GET BACK IN THE GAME
AGAIN?
>> COME ON, MOM!
>> Jeff: TINA HAS HER FOURTH.
SHE CAN START WORKING ON IT NOW.
>> GREEN, RED, YELLOW --
>> Jeff: THIS PUZZLE WILL FOOL
YOU.
YOU'LL BE CERTAIN AND THEN
YOU'LL SPIN IT AROUND AND
REALIZE WHOOPS.
>> CRAP.
OKAY.
WILL THAT DO IT?
YELLOW.
THAT'S GOOD.
>> DOES SHE HAVE IT.
>> I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: LAURA THINKS SHE HAS
IT.
RED, YELLOW, PURPLE, GREEN.
YELLOW, RED, PURPLE, GREEN.
PURPLE, GREEN, RED YELLOW.
LAURA WINS, WILL STAY ALIVE TO
SEE DAY 28.
WE'RE NOW LOOKING FOR ONE MORE
SPOT.
IT'S NOW TINA AND VYTAS, THE
LAST PERSON TO FINISH WILL JOIN
THE JURY.
LAURA NOW TRYING TO BLOCK IT AND
SPIN IT.
>> YOU'VE GOT IT, TINA, RELAX.
>> AH!
PUT THE ONE WITH THREE YELLOWS
ON THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: LAURA CLEARLY HELPING
TINA.
NOT HIDING IT.
>> THREE REDS.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, FEELING GANGED
UP ON?
>> TOTALLY.
>> Jeff: TINA IS BACK IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
>> RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: THIS IS TWO MOMS
STICKING TOGETHER TRYING TO MAKE
SURE VYTAS DOES NOT ADVANCE.
ANYTHING HA K HAPPEN IN
"SURVIVOR."
VYTAS GETTING VERY CLOSE ON HIS
OWN.
TINA NOW COMPLETELY CAUGHT UP.
>> PURPLE IS FACING YOU.
THAT A GIRL.
>> Jeff: YOU DON'T WANT TO
LOSE RIGHT NOW.
NOBODY WANTS TO BE OUT OF THIS
GAME AFTER 27 DAYS.
>> RED FACING YOU.
A RED.
>> Jeff: TINA AND VYTAS BOTH
WORKING ON THEIR FINAL BLOCK.
VYTAS NOW LISTENING TO LAURA,
TOO, THIS IS GOING TO BE CLOSE.
>> PURPLE RIGHT THERE!
I THINK YOU'VE GOT IT.
>> I'M DONE.
>> I HAVE IT, TOO.
>> Jeff: HOLD VYTAS.
RED, YELL, LOW PURPLE, GREEN.
PURPLE, GREEN, RED YELLOW.
PURPLE GREEN RED YELLOW.
TINA HAS IT RIGHT.
TINA LIVES TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
>> GOOD JOB.
VYTAS MISSED OUT BY LITERALLY
ONE SECOND.
>> SORRY, BUDDY.
I'M SORRY.
>> GOOD TRY.
>> NO.
>> Jeff: VYTAS WANTS NOTHING
DO WITH LAURA.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: LAURA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
COME OUT HERE FOR THE SECOND
TIME, GET IT DONE RIGHT AWAY,
LET EVERYBODY KNOW "I'M A
THREAT."
TINA, YOU SURVIVE BUT ONLY WITH
THE HELP OF THE OTHER MOM,
LAURA.
VYTAS, YOU CAME INTO THIS GAME
SEEKING SOME CONNECTION WITH
YOUR BROTHER AND SOME
RECOGNITION OF BEING YOUR OWN
PERSON.
AND YET YOU LEAVE HERE BECAUSE
TWO MOMS CONSPIRED AGAINST YOU
TO MAKE SURE YOU DIDN'T MOVE ON
AND IT WORKED.
>> THEY DON'T WANT ME TO MOVE
FORWARD BECAUSE I'M THREATENING
TO THEM.
THAT'S WHY ARAS AND I GOT VOTED
OUT.
WE'RE TWO HUGE THREATS IN THIS
GAME.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU THINK
WILL HAPPEN WHEN YOU GO BACK
WITH HOME WITH YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH YOUR BROTHER.
HE'S BEEN VERY CLEAR HE WANTED
TO HEAL WITH YOU.
HE WANTED TO MOVE FORWARD.
>> I REMEMBER WHEN ARAS CAME
BACK THE FIRST TIME, NOBODY
COULD RELATE TO HIS EXPERIENCE.
LIKE YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED OUT THERE, MAN.
NONE OF US COULD RELATE.
BUT GOING BACK TOGETHER WE HAVE
THIS SHARED EXPERIENCE AND IT'S
GOING TO BRING US A LOT CLOSER,
I'M SURE OF THAT.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, AFTER 27 DAYS
IN THIS GAME, YOUR TIME IS UP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, TOSS YOUR BUFF
IN THE URN, WE'LL SEE YOU BACK.
LOVE YOU, BABY.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> NAMASTE, BITCHES.
(LAUGHTER).
>> Jeff: LAURA, FOR WINNING
THIS DUEL YOU DECIDE WHO GETS
THE CLUE TO THE IDOL.
>> I'M GOING TO GIVE IT TO CIERA
AND SHE CAN DO WHATEVER SHE
WANTS WITH IT.
WHETHER BURN IT, KEEP IT, SHARE
IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, I THINK I'M GOING
TO BURN IT.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN A CLUE
THAT COULD GIVE YOU SAFETY IN
THIS GAME.
THANKS, MOM.
ALL RIGHT, LAURA, TINA,
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU WILL LIVE
TO SEE DAY 28.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS, GRAB
YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
YOU WORKED TOGETHER.
SEE YOU LATER VYTAS.
>> WITH SEVEN PEOPLE IN THE GAME
RIGHT NOW, THE NEXT VOTE AND THE
VOTE AFTER THAT ARE GOING TO BE
THE MOST IMPORTANT.
I HAVE TO GET PAST THIS NEXT
VOTE SO THE WISEST THING I CAN
DO RIGHT NOW FROM MY PERSPECTIVE
IS KEEP EVERYBODY AGAINST KATIE.
>> HEY --
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> KATIE IS THE MOST DANGEROUS
PLAYER RIGHT NOW.
SHE HAS THREE JURY VOTES
ALREADY.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE TO BE
CAREFUL OF.
SHE HAS ARAS, VYTAS' AND TINA'S
VOTE RIGHT NOW.
>> SEALED?
>> THAT'S ALMOST HALF THE VOTES.
WE CAN'T LET HER STICK AROUND.
>> WE HAD THE FIVE-PERSON
ALLIANCE, ME, CALEB, TYSON,
GERVASE CIERA.
WE COULD CONTINUE ALONG THE
COURSE OF THAT FIVE BY VOTING
OUT KATIE BUT YOU DO NOT WANT TO
BE THE GUY THAT WAITED TOO LONG
TO MAKE A MOVE AND GOT
BLINDSIDED YOURSELF.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
BE.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO BE UP TO US
IF WE DON'T MAKE A MOVE.
WE CAN SIT ON OUR HANDS AND HOPE
THINGS WORK OUT OR WE CAN KIND
OF, LIKE, TRY AND TAKE ACTION
AND DO OUR OWN THING.
>> KNOCK IT OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: .
>> IN ALL HONESTY, I FEEL LIKE
TYSON IS GOING TO BEAT US IN THE
END.
>> HE'S BEEN IN CONTROL OF THE
WHOLE GAME.
>> THE WHOLE THING.
>> AND IN THE END IT'S A HUGE
PIECE TO THE PUZZLE.
TYSON'S GOT A HELL OF A RESUME
TO PREACH TO THE JURY WHEN WE
GET THERE.
SO WE'RE THINKING MAYBE BEFORE
WE GET TO THE FINAL 5 WE'LL HAVE
TO PICK OFF SOMEBODY AND THAT
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO BE TYSON.
>> YOU'RE SAFE BECAUSE WE'VE GOT
TO TAKE TYSON OUT.
>> CALEB .
>> WE'RE GONNA BLIND SIDE HIM.
>> CAN I TRUST YOU LIKE ONE
MILLION PERCENT?
>> YES.
>> I'VE BEEN AT THE BOTTOM THE
PAST FEW ABLE TOES.
IT WASN'T LOOKING GOOD FOR ME.
I FEEL LIKE ONE OF THE HER MET
CRABS THAT WALK ALONG THE BEACH
AND YOU HAVE TO TRANSITION FROM
HOME TO HOME AND YOU DON'T HAVE
A SHELL AND THERE'S PREDATORS.
NOW I FEEL LOOK I'VE FOUND A
SHELL.
MY BEST OPTION IS TO WORK WITH
MY ORIGINAL TADHANA MEMBERS AND
GET RID OF TYSON SO I FEEL LIKE
MY OPTIONS ARE GETTING BETTER.
>> BOYS!
>> GIRL!
>> WELL?
>> WELL, WHAT'S NEW.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING?
>> WE'RE THINKING IT'S TIME TO
SHAKE UP THE GAME A LITTLE BIT.
LIKE TYSON.
>> OKAY.
>> RIGHT NOW WE COULD USE KATIE
AS AN EXTRA TYSON VOTE.
>> SO THE FOUR OF US VOTE TYSON
AND TYSON GOES HOME BECAUSE THE
FOUR OF JUST A MAJORITY.
>> SMART.
US THREE FINAL THREE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WE CAN SO OUTSTART THESE
VETERANS RIGHT NOW.
CALEB SAID HE WANTED TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE AND HE WANTED TYSON
GONE AND THAT REALLY THROWS ME
OFF BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE THESE
PEOPLE WHO HAVEN'T PLAYED THE
GAME BEFORE ARE SO WILLING TO
FLIP AND FLOP ON EACH OTHER.
IT'S TOO SKETCHY FOR ME TO
INVEST IN THEM.
SO I TODAY CALEB AND HAYDEN WHAT
THEY WANTED TO HEAR BUT I DON'T
WANT TO WORK WITH PEOPLE LIKE
THAT.
>> AND I'M LIKE, IT DEPENDS.
AND HE GOES WE WANT TYSON GONE.
BUT I PROMISE YOU THIS: I AM
VOTING HOWEVER YOU'RE VOTING
FROM HERE ON OUT, I'LL VOTE
WHATEVER YOU WANT ME TO VOTE.
I DON'T WANT TO GO WITH THEM.
>> YOU HAVE A MUCH BETTER CHANCE
AGAINST ME.
>> I TOTALLY KNOW.
SO IF WE CAN JUST WORK TOGETHER
I HAVE YOUR BACK 100%.
>> I HAVE YOURS AND I TOLD YOU
THAT FROM DAY ONE.
>> BECAUSE I DO NOT TRUST THEM.
>> AND I DON'T, EITHER.
I TRUST GERVASE AND MONICA.
WILL GO WITH US BECAUSE I'VE
SHOWN HER MORE LOVE THAN ANYBODY
ELSE HAS.
SO THAT'S FOUR, WE GOT IT.
THEN WE'RE FLIPPING IT ON HAYDEN
OR CALEB.
>> DEAL.
>> I'M NERVOUS NOW.
I WAS HOPING TO MAKE IT TO SIX
BEFORE I MADE MY MOVE AND LOCKED
THE GAME DOWN BUT I MAY HAVE TO
LOCK IT DOWN EARLIER.
I TRUST MONICA AND I TRUST
GERVASE.
CIERA IS THE MAJOR WILD CARD
HERE.
I HOPE CIERA IS TELLING THE
TRUTH BUT IN THE END IT MAKES
MORE SENSE FOR ME TO GO THAT
DIRECTION ANYWAYS BECAUSE I NEED
CALEB AND HAYDEN OUT AND THE
SOONER THE BETTER.
>> LISTEN TO THIS: CIERA TOLD ME
THEY'RE PLANNING TO VOTE ME OUT.
SHE SAID CALEB CAME UP AND SAID
"YOU READY FOR A BIG MOVE?
WE'RE GOING TO DO IT, TYSON."
SHE SAID SHE TRUSTED ME ENOUGH
THAT ALL I HAVE TO DO IS TELL
HER WHO TO VOTE FOR AND SHE WILL
VOTE WITH ME EVERY SINGLE VOTE
UNTIL THE END.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU WANT TO GET
RID OF CALEB?
>> YEAH.
HE'S SO LIKABLE.
HE'S THE CLEAR SHOT AT THE
MILLION.
>> CIERA SAYS THAT CALEB AND
HAYDEN ARE TARGETING TYSON AND
ARE GOING TO TRY TO VOTE HIM
OUT.
SO NOW WE'RE THINKING OKAY,
WE'VE GOT TO GET RID OF THEM.
TWO DAYS AGO THE FOUR GUYS, WE
HAD CONTROL OF THE GAME.
BUT NOW WE'RE ALL PLOTTING ON
EACH OTHER AND IT MAKES ME
NERVOUS.
BUT AS LONG AS CIERA JUST STICKS
WITH US WE SHOULD BE GOOD.
>> SNEAKY BASTARDS.
>> I KNOW.
I REALLY TRUSTED THEM.
I WAS READY TO GO TO THE FINAL
FOUR WITH THEM.
>> HAYDEN AND CALEB ARE TRYING
TO STIR THE POT AND THEY JUST
GOT SLOPPY.
AND WHEN YOU BREAK YOUR ALLIANCE
LIKE THAT THE GLOVES COME OFF
AND IT'S GONNA GET REAL DIRTY
AND UGLY.
TOMORROW'S GONNA BE HUGE.
>> YEAH.
>> GOOD MORNING!
>> GOOD MORNING.
YOU SLEEP ALL RIGHT?
LITTLE BIT?
>> LITTLE BIT.
>> YOU WANT TO COME GET
WITH ME?
>> OKAY.
>> WE'LL BE BACK.
BYE.
>> SHE WALKED RIGHT BY HERE AND
DIDN'T SAY A WORD.
>> SHE WON'T EVEN LOOK AT ME IN
THE EYE.
CIERA.
>> ME, EITHER.
>> LET'S SEE.
>> THERE IT IS!
>> SO WE STILL GOOD FOR --
>> WE'RE STILL ON FOR --
>> PROMISE?
>> YUP, PROMISE.
>> I GOT LIKE A WEIRD VIBE THIS
MORNING?
>> .
>> YOU DID?
THAT'S OKAY, WE'RE STILL ON
BOARD, ME AND GERVASE TALKED
ABOUT IT LAST NIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA DO IT.
STRAIGHT TO THE FINALS.
>> STRAIGHT TO THE FINALS.
>> I'M SO I DIDN'T GO ALONG WITH
HAYDEN AND CALEB.
I FEEL LIKE I MADE THE RIGHT
DECISION AND I TRUST TYSON
BECAUSE TYSON KNOWS, A, THEY'RE
GUNNING FOR HIM.
B, I SAVED HIM AND, C, HE
DOESN'T WANT TO BE SITTING NEXT
TO THEM AT THE END ANYWAY.
SO I FEEL LIKE I'M IN A GOOD
SPOT COME NEXT TRIBAL.
TRIBAL.
OKAY.
"ARE YOU ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY?
DO YOU HAVE A GRIP ON THIS GAME?
YOU'D BETTER HOLD ON FOR DEAR
LIFE OR TONIGHT YOU COULD LOSE
YOUR FLAME."
>> OOH!
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> THIS MORNING I SAW CIERA AND
TYSON RUN OFF INTO THE WOODS
THEN I STARTED THINKING, YOU
KNOW WHAT?
WHAT IF CIERA TELLS TYSON, HEY,
THOSE GUYS ARE GOING TO BLIND
SIDE YOU.
AND I STARTED TO GET PARANOID
BECAUSE I REALIZE IF CIERA
FLIPPED WE COULD BE IN BIG
TROUBLE HERE.
>> SO WE'RE GOING TYSON, RIGHT?
>> WE ARE, THAT'S --
>> THAT'S THE PLAN.
>> YEAH.
BUT WHEN THEY LEFT THEY WERE
KIND OF LOOKING OUT OUR
DIRECTION.
>> IT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
>> YEAH, ME, TOO.
>> WHY IS SHE SO CHUMMY WITH
TYSON?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DO YOU THINK SHE WOULD GO
WITH TYSON?
>> I THINK POTENTIALLY.
>> BECAUSE IF SO THEN ONE OF YOU
COULD BLIND SIDE HER INTO GOING
-- IF WE DON'T HAVE HER VOTE.
I THOUGHT VOTING TYSON WAS THE
BEST OPTION AND IT WAS GOING TO
BE SMOOTH SAILING BUT NOW THAT
THERE'S SUSPICION ABOUT CIERA
THERE MAY HAVE TO BE A PLAN "B."
>> WE NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT
WE'RE IN THE MAJORITY.
>> I FEEL LIKE AT THIS POINT
EVERYTHING'S ALL UP IN THE AIR
AND NO ONE IS SAFE SO THIS
CHALLENGE IS HUGE.
AND IF CIERA DOESN'T WIN
IMMUNITY SHE COULD BE IN
TROUBLE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
MONICA.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
EACH GOING TO HOLD ON TO A ROPE
HANDLE.
IT'S ATTACHED TO A BUCKET.
INSIDE THE BUCKET IS 25% OF YOUR
BODY WEIGHT.
AS THE CHALLENGE GOES ON, YOU'LL
BE UNABLE TO BEAR THAT WEIGHT,
THE ROPE WILL UNSPOOL, THE
BUCKET WILL DROP, YOU'RE OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
BUT THERE IS A TWIST.
IF, AFTER 29 DAYS, YOU FEEL SO
SECURE THAT YOU DON'T NEED
IMMUNITY TONIGHT YOU CAN SIT IT
OUT AND FEAST.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: BARBECUE STEAK,
BARBECUED CHICKEN, BARBECUED
SAUSAGE.
>> MAN, THAT SMELLS GOOD.
>> I SMELLED IT.
>> I SMELLED IT, TOO!
>> Jeff: IT'S AN INDIVIDUAL
DECISION.
YOU CAN TAKE A WHITE ROCK AND A
BLACK ROCK.
TAKE ONE OF EACH.
HOW GOOD DO YOU FEEL IN YOUR
ALLIANCE?
GOOD ENOUGH TO EAT?
>> THIS SUCKS!
>> Jeff: BLACK MEANS I DON'T
NEED IMMUNITY, I'M EATING.
WHITE SAYS I'M COMPETING.
STICK YOUR RIGHT HANDOUT.
REVEAL.
TYSON IS GOING TO EAT, GERVASE
IS GOING TO EAT AND CAREER A IS
GOING TO EAT.
HAYDEN, CALEB, MONICA AND KATIE
WILL COMPETE.
PEOPLE WHO ARE EATING TAKE A
SPOT OVER HERE.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
THIS IS GOING TO BE INTERESTING.
ALL RIGHT, SKWRERS ARE A, TYSON,
CIERA HAVE CHOSE ON THE SIT OUT
THIS CHALLENGE.
THEY WILL START EATING WHEN THE
CHALLENGE STARTS AND YOU CAN
CONTINUE EATING UNTIL THE
CHALLENGE ENDS.
EVERYBODY -- HOLD ON.
HOLD ON.
EVERYBODY PUT YOUR HANDS ON THE
HANDLE.
CLICK IT BACK AND RELEASE THAT
SPRING.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY'S IN
POSITION.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
START EATING.
>> HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: THERE IS 25% OF YOUR
BODY WEIGHT IN EACH BUCKET.
YOU'LL KNOW YOU'RE STARTING TO
GET IN TROUBLE WHEN YOUR BUCKET
STARTS TO LOWER.
THAT MEANS THAT ROPE IS
UNSPOOLING.
SEVEN PEOPLE CAME HERE TO
COMPETE, THREE OPTED OUT.
LEAVING KATIE, HAYDEN, MONICA
AND CALEB TO DUKE IT OUT.
ALWAYS INTERESTING WHO WILL
CHOOSE TO NOT EVEN COMPETE FOR
THE ONE THING THAT KEEPS YOU
SAFE WITH SEVEN PEOPLE LEFT.
>> THAT'S VERY TENDER.
>> Jeff: KATIE'S BUCKET
STARTING TO DROP A LITTLE.
HOW'S THE FOOD.
>> DELICIOUS TO THE TASTE AND
VERY DESIRABLE.
KEEP IT UP, GUYS.
>> Jeff: MONICA HAS WON TWO
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITIES.
SHE WOULD LOVE TO ADD THAT
NECKLACE ONCE AGAIN.
>> LISTEN, I'M HERE TO SHOW MY
KIDS.
THEIR DAD IS MADE OF GRIT BUT
SO'S THEIR MOM.
>> Jeff: THAT'S PART OF THIS
ADVENTURE FOR YOU, ISN'T IT?
>> WHOLEHEARTEDLY.
SHOW THE KIDS MORE THAN ONE BAD
ASS LIVES IN OUR HOUSE.
>> WE'RE GONNA BE HERE A WHILE.
>> Jeff: BEEN OUT THERE TEN
MINUTES.
IT'S GOT TO SEEM LIKE AN HOUR.
>> IT HURTS.
>> YEAH, IT DOES.
>> (BELCHES).
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, DOES IT BUG
YOU A LITTLE BIT THAT THEY FEEL
SO CONFIDENT THEY'RE GOING TO
EAT?
>> IF I LOSE THIS CHALLENGE THEN
I'LL BE A LITTLE BIT UPSET.
>> AT US?
>> Jeff: MONICA'S BUCKET HAS
NOT MOVED AT ALL.
KATIE'S HAS DROPPED A BIT.
HAYDEN'S DROPPED A BIT.
CALEB HAS DROPPED A BIT.
HAYDEN, CALEB, AND KATIE RIGHT
BACK UP TO THE TOP JUST LIKE
THAT.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> I HOPE THEY GO FOR, LIKE, AN
HOUR.
>> SWEET TEA OR COKE?
>> ICED TEA.
I'LL DRINK ONE FOR YOU.
>> SHUT UP.
>> Jeff: KATIE'S BUCKET
STARTING TO DROP A LITTLE.
CALEB'S BUCKET STARTING TO DROP.
KATIE'S BUCKET STARTING TO LOWER
EVEN MORE.
KATIE CAN HOLD ON NO LONGER.
KATIE IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE
AND WE ARE DOWN TO THREE.
HAYDEN, MONICA AND CALEB.
CALEB, GET UNDER YOUR SKIN AT
ALL?
THREE PEOPLE ARE SAYING "I KNOW
WE'RE NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> OH, YEAH, AT THIS POINT THE
WAY MY HANDS ARE HURTING.
BUT IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> SKIN IS TEARING OFF THE
HANDS.
>> Jeff: CALEB, NOT ONLY ARE
THEY EATING, THEY'RE HAVING A
GOOD TIME.
THEY'RE LAUGHING!
PERFORM MORE ME!
SHOW ME BLOOD!
BRING ME SOME MORE MEAT!
>> JEFF, BLOOD WILL BE DRIPPING
INTERPRET THE I SOON.
>> AWESOME.
MINUTES NOW.
HAYDEN'S BUCKET SLIPPING AGAIN.
THAT BUCKET IS ALMOST HALFWAY
DOWN.
MONICA'S BUCKET IS STARTING TO
DROP A LITTLE.
HAYDEN SAYS "I'M HERE TO PLAY,
LET ME JUST REMIND YOU."
EVEN WITH THOSE BLISTERS HAYDEN
IS WRENCHING THAT BUCKET BACK
UP.
EVERYBODY PULLING THEIR BUCKETS
BACK UP.
THAT IS DETERMINATION.
AND JUST LIKE THAT CALEB'S
SLIPPING AGAIN.
>> I'M STARTING TO BLEED.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
VOTING YOU OUT.
>> YUP.
>> SORRY GUYS.
>> GOOD JOB, CALEB.
>> CALEB, LET IT DOWN.
CANNOT TAKE THE PAIN ANYMORE.
DEFINITELY SHOWED HE IS WORTHY
BUT FELL SHORT.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS HAYDEN AND MONICA.
MONICA HAS WON TWO INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITIES.
HAYDEN HAS WON NONE.
NO SOONER SAID THAN HE WRENCHES
IT BACK UP AGAIN SENDING ANOTHER
SIGNAL TO MONICA "YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO GET THIS WITHOUT
WORKING FOR IT."
MONICA INCHING RIGHT BACK TO THE
TOP.
HAYDEN'S BUCKET SLIPPING AGAIN.
HAYDEN'S GOING TO HAVE TO REALLY
DIG NOW.
IT IS CRUNCH TIME FOR HAYDEN.
MONICA LOOKING VERY GOOD.
THAT BUCKET IS STILL AT THE TOP
OF HER ROPE.
>> MOM POWER!
>> Jeff: HAYDEN SLIPPING A
LITTLE MORE.
DANGEROUS.
ANYTHING LEFT IN THAT TANK RIGHT
NOW IS WHEN YOU USE IT.
>> COME ON, HAYDEN, CRANK THAT
BACK UP, MAN, LET'S GO.
BACK TO THE TOP.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN SLIPPING A
LITTLE MORE.
HAYDEN LETS GO.
MONICA WINS HER THIRD INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
PEACE OUT!
>> GOOD JOB, MONICA.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN FINISH WHAT'S
IN YOUR MOUTH.
THAT'S IT.
WE'RE DONE.
>> YOU DID UNBELIEVABLE.
MONICA, COME ON OVER.
ONCE AGAIN, MONICA IS SAFE.
>> GOOD JOB, MONICA!
>> Jeff: THIRD INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY WIN.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, GERVASE,
TYSON, CIERA, KATIE, HAYDEN AND
CALEB, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT, SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL HAVE TO
FIGHT TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> GOOD JOB, MONICA.
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> WHAT IS THAT, THREE MONICA
CULPEPPER?
>> I WANT TO HEAR ABOUT STEAKS.
TELL ME ABOUT A CHICKEN.
>> THE STEAK WAS THE BEST.
>> WAS IT?
>> IT WAS SO SOFT.
LIKE, NO GRISTLE, NOTHING.
>> AND THE CHICKEN?
>> THE CHICKEN THERE WAS --
>> I LIKED THE SKIN ON THE
CHICKEN.
>> THERE WAS CHICKEN BREAST AND
DRUMSTICKS.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE BREAD?
THE BREAD?
WERE THE ROLLS GOOD?
>> THE LOAF WAS GOOD.
>> WE WALK INTO THE CHALLENGE
TODAY AND YOU CAN EITHER COMPETE
OR CHOOSE TO EAT AND I DON'T
WANT TO BE THE GUY THAT GETS
BLINDSIDED AND GOES HOME SO I
WANT TO COMPETE.
TYSON, GERVASE, CIERA, THEY ALL
CHOSE TO EAT AND IT'S KIND OF
TELLING.
THEY OBVIOUSLY FEEL VERY
COMFORTABLE AND IF THE THREE OF
THEM FEEL THAT GOOD MAYBE
THEY'RE ALL WORKING TOGETHER TO
GET RID OF ONE OF US.
>> WHEN I SAW THEM OVER THERE
TODAY EATING IT MADE ME WONDER.
>> I AGREE.
I DON'T THINK I CAN TRUST HER.
AND I KNOW I CAN TRUST CALEB AND
I KNOW I CAN TRUST YOU.
BUT IT'S THREE AGAINST FOUR.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'M IN A PREDICAMENT.
I COULD BE ON A SINKING SHIP SO
NOW I'M BACK-PEDALING THINKING
OKAY, I HAVE TO SCRAMBLE AND
MAKE A NEW PLAN.
>> I THINK CIERA'S ALREADY WENT
WITH TYSON.
WE JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE WE
HERE IN THE MAJORITY, DUDE, I
DON'T CARE HOW WE DO IT.
>> WHAT IF WE JUST FLAT OUT ASK
TYSON.
>> ASK HIM WHAT?
>> IF THEY'RE PLANNING ON BLIND
SIDING ONE OF US.
SEE WHAT HIS REACTION IS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND THEN WE CAN EVEN SAY
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY PLAYING US
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
>> YEAH.
>> AND WE ALL VOTE AS ONE.
>> I'M JUST NOT FEELING 100% ON
THEM.
>> I'M NOT, EITHER.
>> CIERA DID IT TO HERSELF.
>> HEY, WE'VE GOT TO BE ON THE
SAME PAGE.
>> RIGHT.
>> LIKE, SERIOUSLY.
UM, WE FELT LIKE YOU, CIERA AND
GERVASE ARE TRYING TO GET ONE OF
US.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: .
>> THAT'S WHAT I FEEL.
>> I WAS KIND OF UNDER THE SAME
IMPRESSION THAT YOU GUYS WERE
OUT TO GET ME.
CIERA BLAMED THAT ON YOU GUYS.
>> THE ONLY REASON IS BECAUSE WE
THOUGHT YOU WERE TRYING TO GET
US.
IN MY HEAD I'M THINKING IF
TYSON'S AFTER ME WE HAVE TO GET
HIM FIRST.
>> RIGHT.
>> NOW I DON'T WANT THAT.
>> CIERA'S BEEN PULL MEGAASIDE
LIKE "WE GOT TO TALK."
I'M LIKE THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE
WHY YOU GUYS WOULD DO THAT.
I'M LIKE WE'VE GOT IN THE THE
BAG, WHY ARE THEY (BLEEP)ING IT
UP?
SO I WAS STILL SKEPTICAL OF IT
ALL.
HAYDEN AND CALEB PULLED ME ASIDE
AND WERE LIKE "CIERA'S PLAYING
BOTH SIDES."
WHEN I THINK ABOUT IT IT MAKES
SENSE, WHY WOULDN'T SHE?
SHE SEEMS LIKE A SMART ENOUGH
GIRL AND I KNOW SHE'S A GOOD
LIAR.
IN HER MIND SHE'S PROBABLY
THINKING BY PITTING THE GUYS
AGAINST EACH OTHER SHE CAN STICK
AROUND A LITTLE LONGER AND THAT
WAS A SMART MOVE ON HER PART.
BUT NOW I'M FEELING LIKE SHE'S
TOO SNEAKY AND TOO SMART AND TOO
DECEIVING TO BE IN THE GAME
ANYMORE.
>> IT'S GOT TO BE CIERA.
>> PROMISE ME I WON'T HAVE THE
MAJORITY ON MY NAME.
>> YOU WON'T.
>> OKAY, LET'S DO IT.
CIERA GUARANTEED.
>> OKAY.
WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE.
>> THE PROBLEM IS I DON'T TRUST
HAYDEN AND CALEB, EITHER.
WHO KNOWS?
THEY COULD BE TRYING TO MAKE ME
FEEL COMFORTABLE AND THEN POW I
GET HIT WITH A HEART BREAKER.
SO I MIGHT HAVE TO PLAY MY
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT'S THAT LITTLE ADDED BIT OF
INSURANCE IN CASE SOMETHING
SCREWY HAPPENS.
>> I BELIEVED HIM.
>> I DO, DO YOU?
>> YEAH, I FELT LIKE HE -- HE
WASN'T EXACTLY SCRAMBLING.
TYSON'S TELLING US HE'S STILL
WITH US BUT I'M NOT SURE I BUY
IT 100%.
HAYDEN FEELS MORE COMFORTABLE
WITH IT THAN I DO.
I'M CITY THINKING IS HE STILL
PLAYING US?
IS HE PLANNING SOMETHING?
IS HE NOT.
>> SHE HAS NO IDEA.
SHE'S BEEN LAYING AROUND
SLEEPING.
>> IT'S WAKE UP TIME.
WAKE UP.
>> WAKE UP TIME.
>> I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" ANYTHING CAN GO WRONG
BUT HOPEFULLY EVERYBODY'S ON
BOARD AND CIERA'S GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
SHE SHOULD HAVE PICKED A SIDE
AND STUCK WITH IT.
>> THE BOYS JUST APPROACHED ME
AND SAID THEY'VE BEEN GETTING
SKETCHED OUT BECAUSE THEY'VE
BEEN GETTING A WEIRD VIBE FROM
US SO THEN THEY THOUGHT THEY
WERE GETTING BLINDSIDED SO THEY
STARTED GUNNING FOR US.
THEY CAME TO ME WITH THIS INFO.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HERE'S THE THING, WHO DO WE
VOTE OUT?
CIERA OR CALEB?
BECAUSE IT SOUNDED PRETTY
PLAUSIBLE WHAT THEY SAID.
TEENAGE MOM?
HELL RAISER?
SHE CAN LOOK IN YOUR EYES AND
LIE BETTER THAN ANYBODY.
>> OH, YEAH, OH, YEAH.
I AGREE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN EVERYTHING IS
BLOWN TO PIECES.
SOMEBODY'S LYING IN THIS.
EITHER HAYDEN AND CALEB OR
CIERA.
>> THEY TOLD ME HOW THEY WERE
GOING TO VOTE, THEY HADN'T COME
TO ME WHICH EITHER MEANS THEY'RE
TRYING TO DRAW VOTES OFF OF THEM
BY THROWING THEM ON CIERA OR
TELLING THE TRUTH.
YOU TELL ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
I DON'T KNOW WHO TO TRUST!
AT THESE TIMES IT JUST COMES
DOWN TO YOUR GUT AND THAT'S
SCARY.
BECAUSE YOU PUT YOUR TRUST IN
THE WRONG PERSON, YOU'RE GOING
HOME!
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ARAS AND HIS BROTHER VYTAS.
ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
HAYDEN, WHEN YOU HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO SIT OUT SO YOU
CAN EAT AND THREE PEOPLE TAKE IT
AND FOUR DON'T, IT SHOWS THAT
THERE IS NOT HARMONY.
>> RIGHT.
NO DOUBT.
AND IT TELLS YOU WHO FEELS
COMFORTABLE AND WHO DOESN'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE RIGHT AWAY.
I MEAN, I CAN SHOW YOU MY HANDS.
>> Jeff: HOLD THOSE HANDS UP
FOR ME.
I WANT TO SEE THEM.
>> THEY DON'T EVEN LOOK AS BAD
AS THEY DID BECAUSE THE BLISTERS
HAVE FOLDED BACK.
THEY WERE BORDERLINE BLEEDING.
>> Jeff: SO HAYDEN, WHEN YOU
COME BACK TO CAMP WITH HANDS
THAT TOMORROW ARE GOING TO BE
WORSE AND TYSON AND GERVASE AND
CIERA ALL COME BACK BELLY FULL
OF FOOD AND IT'S NOT RICE.
>> THERE'S A LITTLE BIT OF
JEALOUSY.
REALLY JUST BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL
AS COMFORTABLE AS THEY DO.
IT'S LIKE, MAN, HOW DO THEY FEEL
SO GOOD THAT THEY'RE ABLE TO SIT
OUT THIS CHALLENGE WHERE I'M ON
THE OTHER SIDE THINKING, MAN,
I'VE GOT TO WIN TODAY OR I COULD
BE GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: CALEB, WAS THERE ANY
OF THE THREE THAT SAT OUT THAT
SURPRISED YOU?
>> NOT REALLY.
NO.
>> Jeff: SO YOU WEREN'T
SHOCKED TO SEE CIERA SIT OUT?
>> NO, I MEAN SHE PROBABLY FEELS
COMFORTABLE AND SHE LIKES TO
EAT.
>> SHE PROBABLY FEELS
COMFORTABLE?
THERE'S NOWHERE TO HIDE!
THERE'S SEVEN PEOPLE LEFT.
CIERA, IT'S A GIGANTIC MOVE.
IT'S ONE THING THERE F THERE'S
11 OR 12 PEOPLE.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY IF I
LOOK AT THE CHALLENGE AND I
DON'T THINK I CAN WIN I'M GOING
TO EAT.
BECAUSE I'D RATHER NOT PLAY AND
EAT THAN LOSE AND NOT EAT.
>> Jeff: TYSON, WERE YOU
SURPRISED THAT YOU, GERVASE AND
CIERA WERE THE THREE THAT SAT
OUT?
>> I WAS SURPRISED THAT MORE
PEOPLE WEREN'T EATING.
I MEAN, I FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH
THE ALLIANCES I'VE MADE AND I
WOULD HOPE WOULD FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH ME SO EVEN
THOUGH ALL OF MY ALLIANCE WASN'T
THERE I TRIED TO ENJOY THE FOOD
AS BEST I COULD.
WHICH WAS A LOT.
>> Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT
TRUST.
GERVASE, SUCH A SIMPLE LITTLE
WORD, ISN'T IT?
>> I TRUST PEOPLE IN MY
ALLIANCE.
I HAVE TO.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
SO I'M HOPING THEY KEEP THEIR
WORD.
I MEAN, WITH THE TRUST AND BONDS
THAT I'VE MADE WITH THE PEOPLE
IN MY ALLIANCE --
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, HE LOOKED
RIGHT AT YOU.
HE SAID "I TRUST THE PEOPLE IN
MY ALLIANCE AND I'M HOPING THEY
KEEP THEIR WORD."
>> WELL I THINK GERVASE REALIZE
THERE IS' BEEN TIMES THAT, YEAH,
I'VE BEEN PARANOID BUT I THINK
WE TRUST ONE ANOTHER.
>> Jeff: SO CIERA, THAT CAN'T
FEEL GREAT, TWO GUYS BEHIND YOU
LOOKING AT EACH OTHER GOING
"WELL, WE'RE GOOD."
I DON'T SEE ANYBODY TAPPING YOUR
SHOULDER?
>> IT FEELS LIKE CRAP.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE PART OF AN
ALLIANCE AND TO HEAR GERVASE AND
HAYDEN ARE CLOSE SECONDS BEFORE
WE'RE ABOUT TO VOTE I FEEL LIKE
THERE'S AN UNDERCOVER MESSAGE OR
WHO KNOWS WHAT?
>> Jeff: TYSON, FOR TONIGHT'S
VOTE, WOULD YOU BE SHOCKED IF
YOU WERE VOTED OUT?
>> I COME INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL
HOPING FOR THE BEST BUT
EXPECTING THE WORST SO, YEAH,
I'D BE SHOCKED.
BUT THAT'S "SURVIVOR."
SOMEBODY GETS BLINDSIDED AND
SOMEBODY GETS SHOCKED AND IT
HAPPENS ALMOST EVERY TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: CALEB, HOW ABOUT YOU?
DO YOU THINK THERE'S GOING TO BE
A BLIND SIDE TONIGHT?
>> YES, I DO.
>> Jeff: CIERA, WOULD YOU BE
SHOCKED TONIGHT IF IT WAS YOU.
>> I WOULD TOTALLY -- I WOULD BE
COMPLETELY SHOCKED BECAUSE I
FEEL LIKE AS FAR AS MY ALLIANCE
GOES I'VE BEEN 100% HONEST,
PROBABLY OVERLY HONEST SHARING
INFORMATION AND I PUT MY TRUST
IN THEM 100%.
SO IF IT IS ME TONIGHT THEN IT
WOULD BE A HUGE BLIND SIDE AND
THE PARANOIA OF THAT IS ALWAYS
THERE AND IT'S HIGHER THAN EVER.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KATIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU JUST RAN YOUR MOUTH WAY
TOO MUCH IN THE PAST TWO DAYS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> JEFF?
JEFF, IT'S IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
THAT'S NOT IT.
HOLD THAT FOR A SECOND.
>> SERIOUSLY, DUDE?
>> COME ON, I GOT A LOT OF STUFF
IN HERE.
THERE IT IS.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR TYSON WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SEE CIERA.
CALEB.
CIERA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CIERA, ONE
VOTE CALEB.
CALEB.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CIERA; TWO
VOTES CALEB.
CALEB.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES CIERA, THREE VOTES
CALEB, ONE VOTE LEFT.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. WATER,"
CALEB.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
CALEB, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
>> APPRECIATE IT.
>> Jeff: WELL, WITH AN IDOL
AND A BLIND SIDE IN THE SAME
TRIBAL COUNCIL, THE DECISIONS
YOU MAKE ABOUT WHO TO TRUST FROM
THIS POINT OUT WILL DETERMINE
WHO MAKES IT TO THE END.
THERE IS NO ROOM FOR ERROR.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
"SURVIVOR," TRYING TO CHANGE HIS
FORTUNE IN THE GAME HAYDEN
THROWS EVERYTHING ON THE TABLE.
>> I HOPE EVERYBODY HERE LIKES
SECOND PLACE BECAUSE IF TYSON
GOES TO THE END HE'S WINNING.
>> Jeff: AND IT JUST MIGHT
WORK.
>> TELL ME A MOVE TO MAKE.
>> IF YOU WANT TO GET HIM OUT
IT'S THIS TRIBAL RIGHT NOW.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT WAS
NOT WHAT I WAS EXPECTING.
I WAS SHOCKED THAT MY NAME WAS
ON THERE.
>> CALEB!
>> I KNOW.
>> I FIGURED THAT CIERA WAS
GOING TO GO HOME BUT IT WAS
DEFINITELY A SUCCESSFUL BLIND
SIDE ON THE OTHER HALF'S PART.
>> CIERA FLIPPED ON US.
>> THAT LITTLE CIERA.
>> DUN DUN DUN!