>> 35 DAYS AGO 10 RETURNING
PLAYERS AND THEIR LOVED ONES
DESCENDED UPON THE CAGAYAN
ISLANDS.
HOPING TO PLAY TOGETHER.
>> I'M SO STOKED THAT I GET
TO PLAY WITH ARAS, I WANT TO
GO DEEP INTO THE GAME WITH
HIM.
>> Jeff: BUT INSTEAD THEY
WERE TORN APART.
>> YOU WILL NOT BE PLAYING
WITH THEM.
YOU WILL BE PLAYING AGAINST
YOUR LOVED ONES.
FORCED TO COMPETE AGAINST
EACH OTHER.
>> ARE YOU NO LONGER LOVED
ONES, YOU ARE NOW
EXPECTITIERS, IT WAS THE
BEGINNING OF BLOOD VERSUS
WATER.
>> EACH TRIBE IS TO YOU
GOING TO VOTE SOMEONE OUT.
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: LAURA, LAURA.
>> NOT GOOD.
>> Jeff: AFTER LAURA B AND
CANDICE WERE VOTED OUT OF
THEIR TRIBES, THEIR LOVED
ONES WERE PUT TO THE
ULTIMATE TEST.
>> Jeff: JOHN, YOU CAN TAKE
HER SPOT AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
>> JOHN CHOSE TO STAY IF THE
GAME.
>> I HAVE TO SHOW ALL THOSE
DUMB ASSES HOW BIG A MISTAKE
THEY MADE.
>> Jeff: WHILE YOU ARE PERT
SACRIFICED HIMSELF FOR HIS
WIFE.
>> YOU HAVE NOW PUT YOURSELF
IN A SPOT FOR WHICH YOU HAVE
TO WIN YOUR WAY BACK INTO
THIS GAME.
>> TIME AFTER TIME AFTER
TIME, AND I WILL.
>> BLOOD IS THICKER THAN
ANYTHING, AND LAURA AND I
ARE BLOOD.
>> Jeff: AT TADHANA JOHN WAS
TOREMENTED BY HIS DECISION
TO ABANDON HIS WIFE.
>> IT DEFINITELY TOOK ITS
EMOTIONAL TOLL ON ME LIKE
THE SECOND I-- .
>> Jeff: BUT HE FOUND
SUPPORT WITHIN HIS TRIBE,
SEPARATED FROM THEIR LOVED
ONES, THEY FORMED A NEW
FAMILY BUT IN THE GAME OF
SURVIVOR, BONDS ONLY TAKE SO
YOU FAR.
THEY LOST FOUR CHALLENGES IN
A ROW.
>> GERVASE WINS IT FOR GAGA
LONG, GALANG WINS AND
REMAINS UNDEFEATED.
>> AND WERE STRUGGLING TO
SURVIVE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT COULD
GET ANY WORSE.
>> Jeff: MEANWHILE AT GALANG,
WINNING KEPT THE RETURNING
PLAYERS HARMONIOUS.
BUT EVERY FAMILY HAS A BLACK
SHEEP.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO BE A
PART OF WHAT IS HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW?
>> Jeff: THEIRS WAS COLTON.
>> THIS ISN'T NATIONAL
LAMPOON'S HORRIBLE VACATION.
>> Jeff: HE WAS UP TO HIS
OLD TRICKS, TELLING LIES.
>> GERVASE?
>> Jeff: AND BULLYING.
THIS GROUP OF VETERANS
WOULDN'T STAND FOR IT.
>> SHUT HIM DOWN.
>> HI REALLY HOPED THAT
COLTON HAD CHANGED BUT
YOU CAN ONLY FAKE IT FOR SO
LONG.
>> Jeff: AND AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND ARENA.
>> I CAN'T DO THIS.
>> MEANING ARE YOU QUITTING
AGAIN.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WHEN HE COULDN'T
GET HIS WAY, HE QUIT.
BUT COLTON'S QUITTING WAS
ONLY THE BEGINNING OF WHAT
WOULD TRANSPIRE AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THERE WAS FIGHTING.
>> HE'S SHHING THE WOMEN.
>> YOU, BRAD CULPEPPER.
>> Jeff: EPIC BATTLES.
>> THERE YOU GO.
MARISSA STAYS ALIVE.
>> THAT'S WHY WE DON'T QUIT.
>> Jeff: AND HEART-WRENCHING
GOOD-BYES.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE SURVIVOR, BUT I
LOVE MY WIFE MORE.
>> Jeff: UNTIL THERE WAS ONE
LEFT, LAURA M.
SHE DOMINATED REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
>> LAURA STAY AS LIVE.
LAURA M.
LAURA WINS.
>> Jeff: EARNING HER WAY
BACK INTO THE GAME.
AND WAS REUNITED WITH HER
DAUGHTER CIERA.
>> DROP YOUR-- WE ARE
MERGED.
>> Jeff: AFTER THE TWO
TRIBES MERGED.
>> ARE YOU WITH US.
>> Jeff: TYSON AND GERVASE
SAW-- AS THE ULTIMATE
THREAT.
>> BRING YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: AND TOOK THEM OUT
ONE BY ONE UNTIL LAURA AND
HER DAUGHTER WERE THE ONLY
COUPLE REMAINING.
>> WE ARE THE LAST COUPLE.
>> Jeff: KNOWING COUPLES
WERE A TARGET CIERA MADE THE
BIGGEST AND MOST EMOTIONAL
MOVE THE GAME OF SURVIVOR
HAS EVER SEEN.
>> I WANTED TO SIT THE END
WITH MY MOM.
>> Jeff: 11th PERSON VOTED
OUT, LAURA.
>> SHE VOTED OUT HER MOM TO
FURTHER HERSELF IN THE GAME.
AND WITH NO COUPLES
REMAINING, IT WAS THE
RETURNING PLAYERS WHO TOOK
CONTROL OF THE GAME.
WINNING CHALLENGES.
>> MONICA WINS HER THIRD
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: FINDING IDOLS.
>> I THINK I WILL KEEP IT TO
MYSELF.
>> Jeff: AND REVEAL.
AND EVEN PICKING UP A LITTLE
BIT OF LUCK.
>> THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
RESEARCH-- REDUMP-- REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
>> Jeff: AFTER THE DUST
SETTLES THERE WERE FIVE
LEFT.
>> WE ARE IN THE BOTTOM, WE
GET IT, 2 VERSUS 3.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST COUNCIL,
CIERA AND HAYDEN TRIED TO
CONVINCE MONICA TO TURN ON
HER ALLIANCE.
>> MONICA YOU ARE TYSON'S
LAST DOG AND HE IS USING YOU
ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
>> HE HAS MADE FUN OF YOU,
EVIL RUDE THINGS HAVE BEEN
SAID.
>> Jeff: BUT IT DIDN'T WORK.
>> BRING YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: CIERA WAS LEFT ON
THE BOTTOM AND HAYDEN SENT
TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
WELL, AFTER TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNSEL TILL IS CLEAR IT IS
GOING TO BE A BATTLE UNTIL
THE VERY END.
TONIGHT IT'S A FIGHT TO THE
FINISH.
GERVASE, THE SEASON ONE
VETERAN VOWED REVENGE ON THE
COMPETITION AFTER THEY VOTED
OUT HIS NIECE.
>> SHE WALKED OUT OF REDEMP-
TION I PROMISED I WAS GOING
TO GET THEM.
>> I WANT THE MILLION
DOLLARS I WANT THE SOLE
SURVIVOR.
I WANT THIS.
>> Jeff: MONICA, SHE'S
EMERGED FROM HER HUSBAND'S
SHADOW DOMINATING CHALLENGE
AFTER CHALLENGE.
>> BRAD HAS ALWAYS BEEN THE
BREADWINNER IN OUR HOUSE.
AND THIS MOMENT RIGHT NOW
HERE ON SURVIVOR IS ABOUT
ME.
>> Jeff: TYSON THE FORMER
CHALLENGE THREAT INJURED HIS
SHOULDER EARLY IN THE GAME
BUT QUICKLY ADAPTED,
MOTIVATED BY HIS LOVE FOR
HIS GIRLFRIEND.
>> I TOLD MYSELF WHEN RACHEL
LEFT THAT IF I WAS GOING IT
TO STAY, I HAD TO GET TO THE
END.
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY IT WOULD
BE WORTH IT FOR ME TO STAY
HERE.
AND I'M SO CLOSE.
>> Jeff: CIERA, THIS
NEWCOMER STARTED SLOW BUT
QUICKLY BECAME A FORCE IN
THE GAME, EVEN VOTING OUT
HER MOM TO GET THIS CLOSE TO
THE END.
>> I'VE DONE SO MUCH TO GET
MYSELF HERE THIS IS MY TURN
THIS IS MY SHOT.
I'M GOING TO WIN THE MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> Jeff: OVER AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND HAYDEN AND LAURA WILL
BATTLE IT OUT IN ONE FINAL
DUAL WHO WILL PREVAIL AND
REENTER THE GAME.
FIND OUT TONIGHT WHO WILL
WIN THE MILLION DOLLAR PRIZE
AND TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> THAT WAS PART OF THE GAME,
I LOVE YOU GUYS THOUGH.
PUT ME RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
GOOD, GOOD PLAY.
>> I HEARD WHAT YOU WERE
SAYING.
I HEARD IT.
>> WHAT I SAID ABOUT LIKE
YOUR KIDS.
>> TONIGHT DID NOT GO
ACCORDING TO PLAN, HAYDEN
WENT HOME.
I PLANTED THAT SEED WITH
MONICA AND IT DIDN'T WORK.
BUT THE GREAT THING ABOUT
THIS GAME IS REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
>> IT WILL BE AN INTERESTING
DUAL.
>> IT WILL BE.
OBVIOUSLY TOMORROW SOMEONE
COMES BACK IN.
>> SOMEONE COMES BACK IN
TOMORROW.
>> REDEMPTION ISLAND, MY
HOPE IS THAT MY MOM COMES
BACK IN.
AND SO THAT IS AN ALLIANCE
MEMBER THAT I WILL HAVE,
WHOEVER COMES BACK IN I KNOW
WILL BE WORKING WITH ME.
SO I GUESS I HAVE OPTIONS
THAT I'M GOING TO BE GOING
AFTER ALL OF THEM.
>> DOW GUYS WANT THE TARP OR
THE BLANKIE?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SLEEP ON
THE BURLAP RICE BAG.
>> MY BEST SHOT IS GOING TO
BE WITH MONICA AND GERVASE.
AND I MAY HAVE TO USE THAT
IDOL TO KEEP MONICA ON OUR
SIDE I THRUST YOU 100%.
AND YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO
SAY I GOT TYSON AND I GOT
GERVASE.
>> OF COURSE.
>> DID YOU WANT TO OPEN
THAT.
>> CAN I LOOK AT IT?
>> YEAH.
>> OH MY GOSH THAT'S AWESOME.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO PLAY
THIS.
YOU CAN TAKE IT AND GIVE IT
TO YOUR KID.
>> NO, I'M NOT TAKING IT
THAT, THAT IS YOURS.
>> I'M TO THE GOING TO DO
ANYTHING WITH THAT.
THAT WILL SIT IN A BOX UNTIL
I THROW IT AWAY.
>> HAVING SOMEONE COME IN
FROM REDEMPTION AND PARTNERING
UP WITH CIERA.
AND THEY WILL TRY DRAWING
MONICA IN AGAIN.
AND SO GERVASE AND MY GOAL
NEEDS TO BE TO KEEP MONICA
TIGHT WITH US.
>> CAN I SEE YOU FOR
CHRISTMAS?
>> IF THE GUYS REALLY DO
JUST THINK I'M THEIR LAP DOG,
FINE.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO BE
MANIPULATED BY TYSON AND
GERVASE.
BECAUSE GUESS WHAT?
WHOEVER COMES IN FROM
REDEMPTION ISLAND TOMORROW
IS ON HER TEAM.
I WANT TO BE ON BOTH TEAMS.
TWO CHANCES OF GOING TO THE
FINAL THREE.
>> HAYDEN!
>> DARN IT.
>> I KNOW.
>> DANG IT!
WE'RE SO SORRY IT'S YOU.
>> I NEED I HUG.
I SMELL BAD.
>> WE ALL SMELL BAD.
>> THIS IS THE SECOND TIME
I'VE PLAYED A GAME LIKE THIS
AND THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE BEEN VOTED OUT.
AND GETTING VOTED OUT SUCKS.
>> YOU'VE HAVE A LOT TO
CATCH US UP ON.
>> GE-- CIERA WON.
>> NO, ARE YOU KIDDING ME.
>> NO, SHE WAS THE
CHALLENGERS, SHE GOT IT.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT.
>> TRIBAL WAS BRUTAL.
ON ONE SIDE, TYSON GERVASE
ON THE OTHER.
MONICA IN THE MIDDLE.
I THINK WE WERE CLOSE.
BUT HERE I AM, MONICA JUST
LISTENING TO WHAT TYSON SAY,
BUMMER.
>> SOMEBODY ELSE HAS TO GET
IN SHALL DID -- IN ITS'S
TYSON GERVASE MONICA AT THE
END, I'M GOING TO VOTE FOR
JEFF.
>> ONE OF US HAS TO GET BACK
IN THERE.
>> WE HAVE TO.
>> ONE OF US WILL.
>> IT'S TRUE.
>> WHOEVER GETS BACK IN,
FINDS THE IDOL AND CAN
CHANGE THE GAME.
>> THE BEAUTIFUL PART ABOUT
THIS SEASON IS I'M OUT BUT
I'M NOT DONE.
I WIN AT THE DUAL TOMORROW,
I'M RIGHT BACK IN THE GAME.
AND I GET TO COMPETE AGAIN.
I LIKE MY CHANCES.
I REALLY DO.
>> THIS IS IT, YOU YOUR
FINAL DUAL.
WHEN IT IS OVER, ONLY ONE OF
YOU WILL RETURN TO THE GAME.
THE OTHERS WILL JOIN THE
JURY.
DO-OR-DIE.
>> I'VE BEEN DYING TO
DO-OR-DIE FOR A LONG TIME.
>> SO LONG.
>> IT'S A BIG DAY TODAY.
I CAN TASTE THIS.
THERE'S A LOT RESTING ON
TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
SO IF I COME OUT OF
REDEMPTION ARENA WITH ONE
OUNCE OF ENERGY IN ME, I DID
SOMETHING WRONG.
>> WE WILL NEVER SEE THIS
HOME AGAIN.
>> BUT WE'LL FEVER FORGET
IT.
>> I'M SO READY FOR THIS
DUAL TODAY.
I THINK CIERA IS WAITING FOR
THE CALL VARY COME IN.
SHE IS THE LONE SOLDIER
WAITING ON THE LEDGE FOR
SOMEBODY TO COME IN.
SO I HAVE TO GET BACK IN THE
GAME.
>> MORNING GUYS!
>> WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR OUR FINAL
DUAL.
TINA, LAURA AND HAYDEN VOTED
OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA AND YOUR FINAL DUAL.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
YOU'RE GOING TO PLACE ONE
FOOT AT THE END OF A
BALANCING BOARD.
AT THE OTHER END A CERAMIC
VASE.
WHEN YOUR VASE FALLS, YOU'RE
OUT OF THE DUEL.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING
WITH THEIR VASE INTACT WILL
REJOIN THIS GAME AND
CONTINUE YOUR GUEST FOR THE
MILLION DOLLARS AND THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
THE LOSERS ARE OUT FOR GOOD.
AND BECOME THE FIFTH AN
SIXTH MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
THIS IS IT.
YOUR FINAL SHOT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO,
EVERYBODY PLACE ONE FOOT AT
THE END OF YOUR BALANCING
BOARD.
WHEN DOW SO YOU WILL RELEASE
THE BRACE THAT IS RIGHT NOW
HOLDING YOUR VASE UP.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON, NICE
AND STEADY, DON'T PANIC,
THERE IS NO SECOND PLATES
TODAY.
ONE WINNER, TWO LOSER,
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO REJOIN
THIS GAME, SOMEBODY'S GOING
TO BE BACK IN THE HUNT FOR A
MILLION DOLLAR CHECK AND THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
THE TWO OTHERS WILL HAVE A
SAY IN WHO WINS BUT THEY'LL
DO IT FROM THE JURY SIDE OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LAURA OFF TO A VERY SHAKY
START.
GOT TO GET IT BACK TOGETHER.
SHE'S WON FIVE OUT OF SIX
DUELS, NOT JUST SURVIVED,
WON.
WOULD LOVE TO JOIN HER
DAUGHTER BACK IN THIS GAME.
EVERYBODY LOOKING REALLY
GOOD.
THIS COULD GO AWHILE
.
>> ANOTHER VERY HOT DAY TINA
IS ROCK STEADY.
HAYDEN STILL VERY STEADY.
LAURA STRUGGLING, LITERALLY
HOPPING AROUND TO SAVE IT.
THAT VASE IS MOVING A LOT.
CAN SHE RECOVER?
DIG, WOMAN.
INCREDIBLE SAVE BY LAURA.
HAYDEN SLIPPED OUT OF
NOWHERE.
HAYDEN BECOMES THE FIFTH
MEMBER OF THE JURY.
HE IS OUT OF THIS GAME.
JUST LIKE THAT WE ARE DOWN
TO TWO MOMS.
IT IS LAURA AND TINA NOW
FIGHTING FOR ONE SPOT TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
>> LET ME HAVE IT, PLEASE.
>> NO WAY, SISTER.
>> I LOVE YOU, BUT THIS IS A
MILLION DOLLAR CHALLENGE,
HONEY.
>> LAURA HAS BEEN STRUGGLING
FROM THE MOMENT WOE STARTED.
BUT SHE IS STILL IN IT ONE
OF YOU WILL BECOME THE SIXTH
MEMBER OF THE JURY.
THE OTHER PERSON IS BACK IN
THIS GAME.
PART OF THE FINAL FIVE AND
JUST LIKE THAT YOU'RE IN THE
HUNT FOR THE MONEY AND THE
TITLE.
THE QUESTION IS WHO IS GOING
TO HOLD OUT THE LONGEST
.
TWO MOMS BATTLING IT OUT.
FINA-- TINA HAS NEVER WON A
DUEL.
SHE NEEDS TO TODAY.
LAURA HAS ONLY LOST ONE
DUAL.
TINA'S LEGS ARE SHAKING AM
YOU HAVE TO MASK THAT PAIN.
YOU HAVE TO OVERCOME IT.
TINA IS FIGHTING THROUGH
PAIN RIGHT NOW.
SHE'S GOT TO FIND A WAY TO
DIG THROUGH THIS.
AN AMAZING SAVE.
LAURA, CAN SHE DO IT?
CAN SHE SAVE IT AGAIN?
LAURA'S VASE DROPS.
LAURA BECOMES THE SIXTH
MEMBER OF THE JURY, TINA
WINS THIS DUEL AND WILL
REMAIN AS THE FIFTH THEN.
>> I'M SORRY, I KNOW YOU
WANTED IT.
I KNOW YOU WANTED IT.
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, YOU WON BIG
BROTHER WHICH IS ITS OWN
BATTLE.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THE TAKE
AWAY FROM SURVIVOR.
>> WHEN YOU'RE OUT HERE, YOU
BEGIN TO APPRECIATE WHAT YOU
HAVE BACK HOME.
LIKE I HAVE AN AMAZING
FAMILY.
YOU KNOW, A BEAUTIFUL
GIRLFRIEND.
AND THAT'S MY BIGGEST TAKE
HOME.
I AM GOING TO GO HOME, TELL
THE FAMILY I LOVE THEM, GRAB
MY GIRLFRIEND, GIVE HER A
BIG KISS.
AND I'M EXCITED TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HAYDEN,
YOU BECOME THE FIFTH MEMBER
OF OUR JURY, WILL YOU HAVE A
SAY IN WHO WINS THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, ON THE WAY
OUT, SEE YOU AT THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> GOOD JOB, HAYDEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GOD BLESS.
LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: LAURA, HOW DO YOU
READ THIS GAME?
IS IT A SUCCESS OR A
FAILURE?
>> THE FAILURE PART OF ME IS,
YOU KNOW, RAISING KIDS AND
TELLING THEM FINISH STRONG,
FINISH STRONG.
AND-- .
>> Jeff: SO YOU DON'T FEEL
YOU DID?
>> NO, AT THIS MOMENT.
>> Jeff: SOME WILL ARGUE
THAT IF YOU ARE LOOKING TO
TEACH YOUR CHILD A LESSON,
THAT THE LESSON OF YOU MUST
WIN OR YOU'RE A FAILURE IS
MAYBE NOT THE RIGHT ONE.
BUT THAT FINISHING STRONG IS
GIVING EVERYTHING YOU HAVE.
YOU DIDN'T WIN, BUT DOES
THAT MEAN YOU DIDN'T FINISH
STRONG?
>> IT'S-- WHAT GOOD IS
WINNING SIX, SEVEN
CHALLENGES IF YOU CAN'T
FINISH IT.
>> MOM, IT'S OKAY.
YOU DID AMAZING.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
I REALLY AM.
YOU HAVE SHOWN ME OUT HERE
HOW TO BE A BETTER FRIEND;
HOW TO BE A BETTER WOMAN.
AND HOW TO BE A BETTER MOM
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
AND I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> HOW CAN YOU WALK AWAY SAYING
YOU LOST AFTER THAT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAURA,
AFTER 36 HARD FOUGHT DAYS IN
THIS GAME, YOUR RUN COMES TO
AN END.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, TOSS YOUR
BUFF IN THE EARN AND YOU
BECOME THE SIXTH MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
>> LOVE YOU, MOM.
>> I LOVE YOU.
BYE, GUYS.
(APPLAUSE)
>> Jeff: .
>> Jeff: TINA, YOU ARE BACK
IN THIS GAME.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF PROBST.
>> Jeff: AND BECAUSE YOU WON
THE DUEL YOU'RE ALSO IN
CHARGE OF WHO GETS THE LAST
CLUE.
YOU CAN GIVE IT TO ANYBODY
WHO'S IN THE GAME AND THAT
INCLUDES YOU.
>> THANK YOU, MY FRIEND.
THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GRAB
YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
AWAIT INSTRUCTION OF YOUR
NEXT CHALLENGE.
>> WHEN MY MOM'S VASE FELL
MY HEART SANK.
I ALWAYS HAD THAT HOPE THAT
MY MOM COULD POTENTIALLY
COME BACK IN IT.
BUT I'M BY MYSELF.
MY MOM'S NOT COMING BACK.
>> YOUR LEG'S LOOK AWESOME.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I'M BACK IN THE GAME OF
SURVIVOR.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
>> I KNOW THERE IS A HUGE,
STRONG ALLIANCE WITH GERVASE,
TYSON AND MONICA.
SO I FEEL LIKE I DEFINITELY
EITHER TO HAVE TO FIND THE
IDOL OR I HAVE TO TRY TO
TALK MONICA INTO GOING IN
WITH THREE GIRLS AND ALL
MOM'S ALLIANCE.
>> IF WE FIND THE IDOL, WE
CAN TAKE THE BOYS DOWN.
LET'S LOOK.
THEY'RE NOT HERE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO YOU FEEL
PRESSURE.
>> I DON'T FEEL PRESSURE AT
ALL.
>> THERE'S A LARGE TREE
BEHIND YOUR CAMP.
SPREAD OUT.
>> LORD HAVE MERCY.
>>> TINA IS A FREAK, BY THE
TIME I'M THINKING SHOULD GI
PUT MY SHOES ON, TINA IS UP
THE TREE, RUNNING THROUGH
BRANCHES, HOPPING FROM LIMB
TO LIMB.
>> OH DEAR, WE'VE GOT TO
FIND IT.
>> A FEW FEET BEHIND YOUR
CAMP, JUST A FEW FEET
OVERHEAD WITH BRANCHES
SPREAD OUT WIDE.
>> MAYBE IT'S NOT THIS TREE.
>> FOR A 50 SOME-YEAR-OLD
WOMAN, SHE HAS NO FEAR.
AND SHE ACTS LIKE SHE'S A
20-YEAR-OLD.
SHE ACTS LIKE SHE'S MY AGE
DOING THAT AND I'M THE OLD
WOMAN DOWN AT THE BOTTOM.
LIKE TINA, BE CAREFUL, CAN I
HELP YOU, LIKE, LIFT YOUR
FOOT.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE THAT TREE
WOULD BE THE PERFECT TREE,
DOESN'T IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW FOR SURE BUT
THERE IS A CHANCE THAT TYSON
ALREADY FOUND THE IDOL.
>> REALLY.
>> TINA WAS KIND OF LIKE THE
LAST PERSON I WANTED BACK
IN.
BUT I DON'T HAVE ANYBODY
ELSE OUT HERE REALLY.
SO I'M GOING TO KEEP WORK ON
MONICA, AND SHE IF SHE AT
ALL WANTS TO WORK WITH ME
AND TINA.
>> I'LL GO GRAB A BUSHEL OF
PLANTAINS.
>> I'LL PEEL.
>> I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ARE YOU STICKING WITH THE
GUYS?
>> IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO
HEAR WHAT YOU Y'ALL HAVE TO
SAY.
>> I NEED TO GET SOME MORE
INFORMATION.
BECAUSE I REALLY DON'T HAVE
ANY.
>> WELL, I'M JUST GOING TO
TELL YOU, THE JURY WILL BE
UGLY.
>> I PROMISE YOU THAT.
>> IT WILL BE.
>> UGLY.
>> EVERYBODY IS PISSED AT
YOU.
>> PISSED AT ME?
>> SO MAD AT YOU.
>> FOR COMING TO REDEMPTION
EARLY, SAYING THAT YOU --
>> THAT IS INSANE.
>> I'M JUST REPEATING.
>> TINA IS VERY
CONFRONTATIONAL AM SHE WILL
STOMP ON MONICA AND SAY LIKE
MEAN, LIKE, IN YOUR FACE
COMMENTS.
AND I'M THINKING WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA.
WE WANT HER TO COME WITH US.
WE DON'T WANT HER TO HATE
US.
>> I DISAGREE WITH TINA AS
FAR AS THE JURY MEMBERS FEEL
BUT.
WHETHER IT'S TRUE OR NOT
TRUE, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT YOU WON THREE
CHALLENGES.
YOU PLAYED AN AMAZING SOCIAL
GAME.
AND THEN AT THE VERY END TO
BE LIKE YOU THOUGHT HE
HAD-- NO, THIS IS PART OF MY
GAME AND I THINK YOU COULD
POTENTIALLY WIN.
>> I KNOW MONICA, AND I KNOW
THAT YOU HAVE TO APPEAL TO
MONICA'S EGO.
YOU NEED TO BE CAREFUL WHAT
YOU ARE SAYING.
YOU NEED TO BE NICE TO
MONICA.
WE WANT MONICA TO FEEL LIKE
SHE'S MAKING THE DECISION ON
HER OWN, NOT BECAUSE WE ARE
DESPERATE AND WANT HER TO
TAKE US TO FINAL THREE.
>> TO MAKE A MOVE AT THIS
POINT AGAINST TYSON AND
GERVASE WOULD BE EPIC.
>> SURE.
>> AND IF YOU DON'T EVER
MAKE A MOVE, THE JURY WILL
NEVER VOTE FOR YOU.
BUT IF YOU MAKE A BIG MOVE
AND NOT ONLY A BIG MOVE, AN
IMPORTANT CLINCHER MOVE, YOU
COULD WIN.
>> FOR THE LAST HOUR I HAVE
BEEN POUNCED ON BY TINA AND
CIERA ON WHY I SHOULD GO
WITH THEM AND DUMP TYSON AND
GERVASE.
I GOT A LOT OF SORTING OUT
TO DO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT DIRECTION
I'M GOING TO GO.
BUT THIS IS A BRUTAL GAME.
>> Jeff: GOOD MORNING, GUYS!
FINAL FIVE.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO
GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, CIERA, I
MUST TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK
UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO PULL ON A ROPE,
LEVELING OUT AN UNBALANCED
TABLE.
YOU WILL RACE OUT COLLECTING
WOODEN BLOCKS BRINGING THEM
BACK ONE AT A TIME,
ATTEMPTING TO PLACE THEM ON
THE TABLE.
IF YOUR TABLE WOBBLES AND
THE BLOCKS FALL, YOU HAVE TO
RESET THEM.
FIRST PERSON TO GET ALL TEN
BLOCKS ON THEIR TABLE WINS
IMMUNITY.
IS SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, GUARANTEED A SPOT
IN THE FINAL FOUR.
LOSERS, AFTER 37 DAYS, YOUR
SHOT AT WINNING THE MONEY
AND THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR WILL FALL JUST THIS
SHORT.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY PULL ON YOUR ROPE
AND PLACE YOUR FIRST BLOCK.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY.
GERVASE HAS TO COME BACK.
TYSON HAS TO COME BACK.
EVEN IF YOU HAVE A BLOCK IN
YOUR HAND, IF YOUR BLOCK
FALLS, YOU GOT TO PUT THAT
BLOCK BACK, THEN COME
RESTACK, THEN GO GET IT
AGAIN.
PART OF THE LEARNING CURVE
OF THIS CHALLENGE IS GOING
TO BE HOW FAST CAN I PULL.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR THAT SPOT
BETWEEN BRAZ ENAND RECKLES
RECKLESS-- BRAZEN AND
RECKLESS.
THE WOMEN ARE DOING GREAT
OUT OF THE GATE, THE GUYS
STRUGGLING.
TYSON HAS HIS SECOND BLOCK,
GERVASE LOOKING FOR HIS
SECOND BLOCK.
TINA WITH THREE, MONICA WITH
THREE, CIERA NOW WITH THREE.
TYSON HAS THREE.
GERVASE TIPS AGAIN, HE'S GOT
TO GO BACK.
MONICA WITH HER FOURTH.
TINA RIGHT THERE WITH HER
FOURTH.
CIERA HAS FOUR.
TINA HAS FOUR, MONICA HAS
FOUR, AND TYSON HAS FOUR.
MONICA DROPS ALL FOUR OF
HERS.
SHE'S GOT TO COME ALL THE
WAY BACK.
THIS OPENS THE DOOR FOR TINA
TO BE IN THE LEAD.
TINA DROPS ALL FOUR OF HERS.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT BETWEEN BRAZEN AND
RECKLESS.
YOU WANT TO BE FAST BUT YOU
DON'T WANT TO BE OUT OF
CONTROL.
EVERYBODY IS STARTING TO
REALIZE HOW SENSITIVE THIS
UNBALANCED TABLE IS.
TINA CAN'T EVEN GET AFOOT
AWAY FROM THEM.
MONICA NOW HAS FIVE.
CIERA NOW HAS FIVE.
TYSON IN THE LEAD WITH SIX.
TINA DUMPS HERS AGAIN.
YOU SEE IT HAPPENING, YOU
KNOW WHEN IT'S TOO LATE,
WHEN THAT TABLE TILTS TOO
MUCH.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF A
MOMENT BEFORE YOUR BLOCKS
FALL BEHIND.
A LOT OF PEOPLE IN THIS.
THERE IS STILL A LOT OF
CHALLENGE LEFT.
YOU HAVE TO GET TEN PLACED.
TYSON HAS THREE EMPTY SPOTS
LEFT ON THAT TABLE.
THAT'S ALL THAT STANDS
BETWEEN HIM AND A SPOT IN
THE FINAL FOUR.
HE GETS A BREAK WHEN CIERA
DAMPS-- DUMPS ALL SIX OF HER
BLOCKS.
MONICA COMING BACK WITH HER
SEVENTH BLOCK.
TYSON COMING CLOSER NOW WITH
HIS EIGHTH.
HE'S BEEN VERY STEADY.
TYSON HAS GOT TWO LEFT.
MONICA HAS THREE LEFT.
GERVASE HAS THREE LEFT.
CIERA PLACES HER SEVENTH
BLOCK.
TINA DUMPS THEM ALL.
HAS GOT TO RESET EVERYTHING.
MONICA HAS HER EIGHTH.
GERVASE HAS HIS EIGHTH.
GERVASE AND MONICA ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO HOPE TYSON SCREWS
UP.
TYSON COMING BACK WITH HIS
NINTH.
TYSON HAS ONE BLOCK LEFT.
CIERA NOT GIVING UP.
SHE'S STARTING TO MOVE A
LITTLE MORE QUICKLY.
AND IN DOING SO SHE DUMPS
EVERYTHING.
MONICA DUMPS ALL OF HERS,
GERVASE DUMPS ALL OF HIS,
GERVASE AND MONICA HAVE TO
RESET ALL THEIR BLOCKS AND
THAT GIVES TYSON THE SPACE
HE NEEDS TO REALLY TAKE HIS
TIME.
TYSON HAS ONE BLOCK LEFT.
AND HE'S INCHING CLOSER AND
CLOSER.
IF HE CAN JUST KEEP THAT
TABLE STEADY.
TINA DUMPS HERS AGAIN.
SHE'S GOT TO COME BACK.
MONICA DUMPS HERS AGAIN.
SHE'S GOING FOR BROKE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
GERVASE WAS ALMOST THERE
WITH HIS NINTH.
EVERYTHING FALLS.
TYSON GETTING CLOSER WITH
THAT TENTH AND FINAL BLOCK.
HE PLACES IT FOR A COUNT OF
THREE, TWO, ONE.
TYSON WINS IMMUNITY AN A
GUARANTEED SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR!
>> GOOD JOB, TY, GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD JOB, BROTHER.
>> COME ON OVER, TYSON.
>> SHOULD I FEEL LIKE I'M
BEING KNIGHTED?
>> IF YOU WANT.
TYSON, SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE FOUR OF YOU,
AFTER 37 DAYS, REDEMPTION
ISLAND IS OVER.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT AND BECOME THE
SEVENTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
SHOULD BE A VERY INTERESTING
AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> I NEVER REALLY IMAGINED
MYSELF IN THIS POSITION WITH
IMMUNITY ON DAY 37.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO
CELEBRATE BECAUSE IT'S NOT
DONE.
WHAT I NEED TO FOCUS ON NOW
IS HOW THE NEXT ONE IS GOING
TO GO.
>> GOOD JOB, TYSON.
I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
>> THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
>> THAT WAS A FUN ONE.
>> IT WAS FUN, HUH.
RIGHT NOW I HAVE THE
IMMUNITY NECKLACE AND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I WOULD DEFINITELY LIKE TO
KEEP THIS IDOL AS A SOUVENIR
AND GIVE IT TO RACHEL.
>> I LIKE THE GETTING ON ONE
KNEE AND BEING KNIGHTED.
>> IT FEELS GOOD.
I CAN RELAX A LITTLE BIT
TODAY.
AND THE MAIN THING IS WHO DO
WE VOTE OUT TONIGHT.
>> I THINK-- SHE CAN'T WIN.
>> YOU THINK THE SMARTEST
MOVE DID TO GET RID OF TINA
TONIGHT OR CIERA TONIGHT.
>> IF I HAD TO PICK WHO I
COULD SIT NEXT TO IN THE
JURY AND BEAT, I THINK I
COULD BEAT TINA BEFORE I
COULD BEAT CIERA.
>> S WHY'S THAT?
>> BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE CIERA
MADE THE BIGGEST MOVE IN THE
GAME.
SHE'S A YOUNG MOTHER WHO HAS
NEVER WON BEFORE.
>> OUR ALLIANCE IS DEBATING
TINA VERSUS CIERA RIGHT NOW.
AND I WILL PROBABLY LET
GERVASE AND MONICA FIGURE IT
OUT AND GO WITH THEM.
BECAUSE IT TAKES A LITTLE
HEAT OFF ME.
>> I THINK THAT TINA SHOULD
GO BECAUSE EVERY SINGLE
PERSON THUS FAR SITTING ON
THE JURY IS OUT, NOT ONE OUT,
BECAUSE OF HER THAT IS
REALLY HARD TO BEAT AT THE
END.
>> AT THIS POINT IT HAS TO
BE --
>> I AGREE.
IT HAS TO BE --
>> AT FIRST I THOUGHT MAYBE
TINA AND THEN I THOUGHT
MAYBE IT'S BETTER IF CIERA
GOATS.
>> I DON'T WANT TO MAKE THIS
CHOICE.
I WANT YOU GUYS TO MAKE IT.
>> IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
TO ME, I SEE MERIT ON BOTH
SIDES.
>> I WANT TINA TO GO HOME
FIRST.
I THINK IT'S CRITICAL TO OUR
GAME THAT THE PERSON WITH
THE MOST FRIENDS ON THE JURY
GOES HOME NOW.
>> I THINK CIERA IS A MORE
DEADLY PLAYER IN THIS GAME.
I DO NOT TRUST HER.
THAT'S WHY I THOUGHT SHE
NEEDED TO GO.
THE CHICK JUST LIES
CONSTANTLY AND SHE'S GOING
IT TO CONTINUE TO TRY TO
WORM HER WAY INTO PEOPLE'S
HEADS AND DO WHAT SHE HAS TO
DOMENT TINA DOESN'T HAVE
THAT SAVVY TO DO IT.
>> I'M TIRED OF BEING
BULLIED BY TINA.
IT'S TIME FOR TINA TO GO.
>> LOOK, I'M TELLING YOU
RIGHT NOW, YOU ARE DOING IT
ON EMOTION.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> YOU JUST SAID IT, YOU ARE
SICK AND TIRED OF TINA
BULLYING YOU.
>> I'M TIRED OF HER BULLYING
ME AND SHE IS THE ONLY
PERSON HERE THAT HASN'T
VOTED ANYBODY ELSE OUT.
>> THAT IS NOT STRATEGY.
>> I HAVE ENOUGH OF THIS
CRAP SHE IS SPEWING TO ME
BECAUSE IT MAKES NO SENSE.
I'M LIKE PUFFING MY CHEST UP
RIGHT NOW TURNING INTO A
BULLY LEANING IN ON HER LIKE
WOMAN, ARE YOU CRAZY?
>> CIERA-- VOTED OUT HER
MOTHER.
>> HER MOTHER IS GOING TO
GIVE HER THE VOTE NO MATTER
WHAT.
>> SHE WROTE HER MOTHER'S
NAME.
I GIVE THAT MORE CREDIT THAN
ANYTHING.
THAT IS A PLAYER IN THIS
GAME.
>> I JUST DON'T FEEL GOOD
ABOUT IT.
>> I'VE BEEN BULLIED AND
BULLIED AND BULLIED THIS
ENTIRE GAME BY EVERYONE.
IT HURTS.
I'M OVER IT I'M DONE.
I'M TIRED OF BEING BULLIED.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> YOU'RE NOT LISTENING
RIGHT NOW.
TINA HAS MONEY.
SHE'S A MILLIONAIRE FROM
THIS GAME.
THAT IS ONE PERSON THEY WILL
NOT MAKE A MILLIONAIRE
AGAIN.
>> IT'S MY TIME AND YOU ALL
NEED ME.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, GERVASE,
IF YOU ARE'S IN AN ALLIANCE
WITH SOMEONE, YOU BETTER BE
NICE BECAUSE IN THE END YOU
REALLY MIGHT NEED THEM.
>> CIERA, WE DID NOT GET THE
JOB DONE TODAY, MY DEAR.
>> NO.
>> MAYBE WE CAN GET IT DONE
ANOTHER WAY.
>> DO TELL.
>> OBVIOUSLY THERE'S ONE
OPTION, ONES THAT'S NOT
SITTING WITH IMMUNITY.
>> THE THING THAT SCARES ME
IS I THINK HE HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> IF HE THINKS I'M 100%
WITH HIM, HE'S NOT GOING TO
THINK I'M WAFERING.
HE'S NOT GOING TO PLAY THE
IDOL FOR GERVASE.
SHE WOULDN'T KNOW WHO TO
PLAY IT FOR, ME OR HIM.
>> IF MONICA IS GOING TO
MAKE A MOVE, SHE'S GOING TO
MAKE IT TONIGHT.
I WOULD LOVE FOR THIS SEASON
TO GO OUT WITH A HUGE UPSET
AND A BIG BANG.
THE CARDS ARE ALL IN
MONICA'S HAND.
>> I'M ONE WHO LIKES TO DO
THE RIGHT THING.
>> AFTER HEARING THAT, YOU
KNOW, MONICA IS WILLING TO
VOTE GERVASE, I THOUGHT TINA,
DON'T MESS THIS UP.
LIKE KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT
AND LET ME HANDLE THE
SITUATION.
>> THE OPTION TO MAKE A MOVE
FOR ANYONE.
>> RIGHT.
>> TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I'M GOING TO OWN IT.
IT'S MY NIGHT.
IT'S MY STRATEGIC MOVE.
>> DON'T GO WITH ME, DON'T
GO WITH GERV, GO WITH
MONICA.
>> THE GIRLS ARE FIGHTING
OVER ME, SALIVATING, TRYING
TO GET MY VOTE.
AND THE BOYS THINK I'M
LITTLE LAP DOG, MONICA, BUT
TONIGHT IT'S MY CALL.
I'M GOING TO SAY WHO GOES
HOME AND I'M GOING TO MAKE
MY CHOICE ON WHAT'S BEST FOR
ME.
>> Jeff: NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBER ITS OF OUR JURY.
ARAS, VYTAS, CALEB, KATIE,
HAYDEN, AN LAURA-- AND LAURA.
SO CIERA, AFTER THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL YOU WERE DOWN
TO AN ALLIANCE OF ONE.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TINA, YOU
IMMEDIATELY GO TO CIERA
KNOWING THAT'S MY BEST
CHOICE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SHE'S MY ONE AND ONLY
CHOICE.
>> Jeff: SO WE HAVE CIERA &
TINA UP AGAINST TYSON,
GERVASE AND THE QUESTION IS,
MONICA, WHERE DO YOU SIT.
BECAUSE FOR THE LAST SEVERAL
DAYS PEOPLE HAVE BEEN GIVING
YOU A LOT OF ADVICE.
YOU NEED TO MAKE A BIG MOVE.
YOU NEED TO BREAK AWAY FROM
THESE TWO GUYS.
>> I FIND MYSELF IN THE
MIDDLE AGAIN.
THE LAST 24 HOURS I'VE FELT
WHAT IT IS LIKE TO BE A
FIRST-ROUND DRAFT PICK.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE BOTH SIDES
WORKING ON ME.
>> Jeff: WHO MADE A PITCH TO
YOU TODAY, MONDAY CA, AND
WHAT DID THEY SAY.
>> WELL, THE GIRLS CAME TO
ME HONESTLY AND SAID THIS IS
A CHANCE FOR YOU TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE.
AND LET'S TAKE OUT THE
VILLAIN.
>> Jeff: GERVASE, DO YOU SEE
YOURSELF AS A VILLAIN?
>> IT'S FUNNY, I DON'T KNOW
HOW I GOT PAINTED INTO BEING
A VILLAIN.
I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING
VILLAINOUS THAT I'VE DONE.
I'VE PLAYED THE GAME JUST
LIKE THEY'VE PLAYED THE
GAME.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE KEPT MY
WORD TO MY ALLIANCE.
AND THOSE ARE THINGS THAT
GOOD GUYS DO.
>> Jeff: CIERA, WHAT'S YOUR
PITCH.
>> OKAY, WOMAN TO AM WAS, I
WANT TO COME TO YOU AND
BASICALLY LET YOU KNOW,
SINCE THE SECOND I MET UP
WITH THESE BOYS IT'S BEEN
NOTHING BUT MONICA IS AN
EASY VOTE.
MONICA IS AN EASY MANIPULATE,
MONICA IS A PUPPY DOG, SHE
WILL DO WHAT I TELL HER TO
DO.
I'M NOT MAKING THIS STUFF
UP.
I'VE BEEN THERE FOR IT.
AND THEN THERE IS ALSO THE
END OF THE GAME WHEN ARE YOU
SITTING FINAL THREE.
TO GET THE VOTES YOU HAVE TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE.
AND WHAT A BIGGER MOVE THAN
TO GET RID OF THE VILLAIN OF
THE GAME.
WHAT A BIGGER MOVE.
>> I'VE NEVER USED THE TERM
LAP DOG EVER, TO DESCRIBE
MONICA.
I'VE SAID I'VE GOT MONICA,
MEANING SHE'S WITH ME, I
TRUST HER, SHE'S IN MY
ALLIANCE.
SHE'S ANOTHER PERSON THAT
WILL VOTE WITH US.
>> Jeff: MONICA, THIS IS
TOUGH BECAUSE YOU HAVE
ANOTHER MOM WHOSE'S JUST
THROWING OUT ALL THE DIRTY
LAUNDRY.
AND THEN YOU HAVE THE GUY IN
THE ALLIANCE GOING SHE'S
MAKING IT UP.
>> JEFF, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
EXPLAIN THIS ANY BETTER THAN
THE LAST 24 HOURS HAVE BEEN
EXTREMELY DIFFICULT.
BECAUSE IT'S ARGUMENTS THAT
ARE CONTINUALLY BREAKING
DOWN MONICA.
I MEAN YOU COME AWAY FEELING
LIKE I JUST WANT TO DIE
INSIDE.
IT'S REALLY HARD OUT HERE.
IT HAS NOT BEEN UNTIL THE
LAST DAY THAT IT'S GOTTEN TO
BE A LITTLE BIT-- GOTTEN TO
ME A LITTLE BIT.
AND TONIGHT IS MY STRATEGIC
MOVE.
THIS IS MY MINUTE, AND MY
TIME TO LET PEOPLE SEE WHAT
IS THE BEST STRATEGY, NOT
FOR THEM, NOT FOR THEM BUT
FOR MONICA, AND NOT ANYBODY
ELSE.
>> Jeff: GERVASE, THOSE ARE
SCARY WORDS.
>> YEAH, MY HEART JUST
DROPPED OUT OF MY CHEST.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS
TIME TO VOTE, CIERA, YOU'RE
UP.
>> I LOVE PLAYING THE GAME
WITH YOU.
I HAVE SO MUCH RESPECT FOR
YOU, BUT TONIGHT IT'S ABOUT
ME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, TONIGHT IS
THE LAST NIGHT YOU CAN PLAY
IT
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL TONIGHT
IS THE LAST NIGHT YOU CAN
PLAY IT. >> .
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
THIS IS THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, ANY VOTES CAST FOR
GERVASE WILL NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
GERVASE, DOES NOT COUNT.
GERVASE, DOES IN THE COUNT.
CIERA.
15th PERSON VOTED OUT, THE
7th MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
CIERA, THAT'S TWO, THAT'S
ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
CIERA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR TO YOU GO.
>> BYE, GUYS.
>> Jeff: CONGRATULATIONS,
YOU'VE MADE IT TO THE FINAL
FOUR.
TOMORROW YOU'LL COMPETE IN
YOUR FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
TRY TO GET A GOOD NIGHT'S
SLEEP.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED IT GRAB
YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP, GOOD
NIGHT.
>> I HAD PLANS I PUT INTO
MOTION AND IT DIDN'T WORK
OUT.
BUT I KNOW I'VE PLRBED SO
MUCH MORE THAN I EVER
THOUGHT I WOULD.
I THOUGHT I WOULD GO, DAY
ONE, I THOUGHT MY MOM WOULD
BE HERE WITH A PAST ME.
AND I BEAT HER.
I'M LEAVING WITH SO
MUCH CONFIDENCE AND STRENGTH
AND I'M SO HAPPY WITH THE
WAY I WENT OUT, FIGHTING.
I FEEL I DID ALL I COULD DO.
I HAVE GOT TO SAY, YOU ALL
SHOCKED ME ON THAT ONE.
>> I WAS SO NERVOUS GOING
INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
I WAS ABSOLUTELY SHOCKED
WHEN IT WAS CIERA.
SO ONCE AGAIN I'M GOING TO
HAVE TRY AND WIN IT, THE
CHALLENGE TOMORROW.
>> WHAT DOW WANT TO ADD.
>> IN HERE I'M GOING PLAY MY
IDOL.
>> I KIND OF FIGURED THAT
YOU WERE GOING TO GIVE IT TO
GERVASE TONIGHT.
>> I'M IN THIS WITH TYSON
AND GERV, AND I WALKED AWAY
FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL
BLINDSIDED.
I WOULDN'T HAVE PLAYED AN
IDOL UNLESS THEY THOUGHT I
WAS 100% WITH THEM.
SO NOW MY STRATEGY IS TO
REGROUP, TO WIN THAT FOURTH
IMMUNITY TOMORROW, SO THAT I
CAN BE IN CONTROL OF MY OWN
DESTINY
.
YOU DON'T GET TO SEE THAT
EVERY DAY.
>> I'M REALLY, REALLY PROUD
THAT I'M HERE ON DAY 38,
THAT I DEFINITELY, 100%
CONVINCED THAT IF I DO NOT
WIN THIS CHALLENGE TODAY,
THERE'S NO MORE OPTIONS FOR
TINA.
THE ONLY WAY THAT I'VE GOT A
CHANCE IN THIS GAME TO GET
IN THE FINAL 3 IS TO WIN
TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
>> I LOOKED OVER, WAS IT
REALLY RED OVER THERE?
>> YES.
IT WAS SPECTACULAR.
AND YOU HAD THE SUN THERE
AND THEN THE MOON THERE, IT
WAS JUST AWESOME.
>> OH LORD.
>> WE'LL REMEMBER THAT.
>> UH-HUH.
>> SINCE THE MERGE, I FELT
SAFE BECAUSE I DID HAVE THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
BUT IDOLS DON'T EXIST RIGHT
NOW.
THEY'RE ALL DONE.
DO-OR-DIE TODAY.
>> IF THERE WAS EVER A TIME
TO WIN A CHALLENGE, THIS IS
IT.
>> WE'RE DOWN TO ONE OF THE
LAST DAYS.
AND NOW I NEED IT MORE THAN
EVER.
IT'S MAKE-OR-BREAK.
DO-OR-DIE RIGHT NOW.
SO THE MOST IMPORTANT PART
OF THE GAME IS STILL TO
COME.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE
INTERESTING, TO SAY THE
LEAST
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WELCOME TO YOUR FINAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
ONE LAST SHOT.
WIN THIS CHALLENGE YOU
GUARANTEE YOURSELF A SPOT IN
THE FINAL THREE AND A CHANCE
TO PLEAD YOUR CASE FOR THE
MONEY.
SHALL WE GET TO IT?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, TYSON,
TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
THE LAST TIME IMMUNITY IS
BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU
WILL RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES COLLECTING BAGS
OF PUZZLE PIECES, TWO AT A
TIME.
YOU'LL RUN THEM UP, DROP
THEM AT YOUR TABLE, THEN
RACE DOWN A GIANT WATER
SLIDE COLLECTING TWO MORE
BAGS.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL SIX YOU
WILL USE THOSE PIECES TO
SOLVE THE PUZZLE.
THE PUZZLE WILL HELP YOU
SOLVE A COMBINATION LOCK.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH AND
RAISE THEIR FLAG WINS
IMMUNITY.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND BECOME THE EIGHTH AND
FINAL MEMBER OF THE JURY.
-- YOUR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO!
FOR IMMUNITY AND A
GUARANTEED SPOT AT THE FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL, SURVIVORS
READY.
GO!
TWO MEN GO ONE WAY, THE TWO
WOMEN GO THE OTHER.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR TWO BAGS,
THEN YOU CAN HEAD TO THE TOP
AND GET RID OF THEM.
THEN YOU HAVE TO HEAD BACK
DOWN.
MONICA HAS HER FIRST BAG.
GERVASE HAS HIS FIRST BAG,
TYSON HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
TINA HAS HER FIRST.
TYSON LOOKING FOR HIS
SECOND.
MONICA HAS HER SECOND.
MONICA WITH TWO BAGS,
GERVASE WITH TWO BAGS.
IT IS MONICA OUT FIRST.
SHE'LL BE HEADING UP THE
STAIRS FIRST.
GERVASE RIGHT BEHIND MONICA.
GERVASE GOING PASS MONICA.
SHE BLOCKS HIM OUT.
WE'VE GOT A CHALLENGE.
NOBODY GOING TO GIVE ANYBODY
AN INCH.
GERVASE DOWN THE SLIDE,
MONICA DOWN THE SLIDE.
TYSON HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
TYSON UP THE STAIRS.
TINA HAS HER SECOND BAG
TYSON DOWN THE SLIDE, HE'S
LOOKING FOR HIS THIRD AND
FOURTH BAG.
THERE ARE SIX TOTAL.
TINA HAS HER SECOND.
SHE REACHES THE TOP.
TINA COMING DOWN.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR
THIRD AND FOURTH BAGS.
GERVASE HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
MONICA HAS HER THIRD BAG.
SHE'S LOOKING FOR NUMBER
FOUR.
TYSON HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
LOOKING FOR NUMBER FOUR.
TINA BANGING UP HER KNEES
GOING FOR HER THIRD BAG.
MONICA HAS HER FOURTH BAG.
TYSON HAS HIS FOURTH BAG.
HE'S HEADING UP.
TINA WITH THREE, STILL
LOOKING FOR THAT FOURTH.
STARTING TO SLOW DOWN.
GERVASE HAS HIS FOURTH BAG.
ONCE AGAIN, MONICA IN THE
LEAD.
SHE'S WON THREE INDIVIDUAL
CHALLENGES ALREADY.
WOULD LOVE TO ADD A FOURTH
RIGHT HERE!
MONICA AN TYSON BOTH DOWN
THE SLIDE, LOOKING FOR THEIR
FIFTH AND SIXTH BAGS.
GERVASE GOES SIDEWAYS DOWN
THE SLIDE.
HE'S NOW LOOKING FOR HIS
FINAL TWO BAGS.
TINA NOW WITH HER FOURTH
BAG.
SHE'S WAY BEHIND RIGHT NOW.
TYSON HAS HIS FIFTH BAG.
MONICA AND TYSON BOTH WITH
ONE MORE BAG LEFT.
TINA REALLY SLOWING DOWN.
38 DAYS, MANY OF THEM SPENT
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND TAKING
THEIR TOLL.
GERVASE HAS HIS FIFTH BAG.
EVERYBODY'S NOW ON THEIR
LAST BAG EXCEPT FOR TINA WHO
STILL HAS TWO LEFT.
FEWSON WITH HIS SIXTH BAG.
GERVASE HAS HIS SIXTH BAG.
MONICA HAS HER LAST TWO BAGS.
TYSON HEADING UP WITH HIS
LAST TWO BAGS.
GERVASE RIGHT BEHIND.
MONICA HEADING UP THE STAIRS.
ONCE YOU'RE UP THERE, START
SOLVING THAT PUZZLE.
MONTHS CA, TYSON AND GERVASE
ALREADY WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLE.
TINA WORKING ON HER FIFTH
BAG, FOLLOWING OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
REALLY SLOWING DOWN.
TINA BOUNCING TO THAT SIXTH
AND FINAL BAG.
YOU MUST FIRST SOLVE THE
PUZZLE, THEN FOLLOW THE
INSTRUCTIONS.
TINA HAS HER SIXTH BAG.
SHE'S HEADING UP.
GERVASE QUICKLY GETTING ON
IT.
TYSON GOING TO IT.
MONICA WORKING THROUGH THE
PUZZLE.
TINA BRINGING UP THE REAR
HAS LOST A LOT OF TIME.
THIS IS A MILLION DOLLAR
CHALLENGE, RIGHT HERE.
THE ONLY WAY TO GUARANTEE
YOU HAVE A SHOT AT THE MONEY
IS TO WIN, RIGHT NOW.
GERVASE DOING VERY WELL VERY
QUICKLY.
TYSON MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS.
MONICA HAS BEEN THE DOMINANT
PERSON IN THE CHALLENGES
THIS SEASON.
WINNING THREE.
TINA WON A DUEL WHEN SHE
NEEDED TO TO GET HER BACK IN
THIS GAME.
IT IS GOING TO COME DOWN TO
WHO CAN FINISH THIS THE
FASTEST.
RIGHT NOW IT IS MONICA AND
TYSON.
THIS PUZZLE CONTAINS CLUES,
THESE CLUES WILL HELP YOU
SOLVE A COMBINATION LOCK.
THAT LOCK WILL RELEASE YOUR
FLAG AND YOU'RE GOING TO THE
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THAT SIMPLE.
AND THAT COMPLICATED.
MONICA CONTINUES TO MAKE
PROGRESS ON HER PUZZLE.
TINA IS DEFINITELY MAKING
SOME PROGRESS.
EVERYBODY IS VERY CLOSE.
TYSON GETTING CLOSER.
GERVASE, YOU NEED TO PICK IT
UP.
TINA STARTING TO FALL OUT OF
IT AGAIN.
MONICA STILL FIGHTING.
TYSON HAS SOLVED THE PUZZLE.
NOW START SOLVING THE CLUES.
EVERYTHING YOU NEED IS
WRITTEN IN THAT PUZZLE.
READ THE CLUES.
THEY WILL TELL YOU THE
INFORMATION YOU NEED TO
SOLVE THE COMBINATION.
TYSON HEADS DOWN THE SLIRD
SEEKING INFORMATION, TO
SOLVE THAT COMBINATION.
GERVASE CLOSE TO FINISHING
HIS PUZZLE.
MONICA VERY CLOSE.
TYSON NOW COUNTING SOMETHING
ELSE, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT DOES HE NEED TO SOLVE
THIS PUZZLE?
TYSON IS BACK.
DOES HE HAVE THE RIGHT
INFORMATION?
GIVES IT A TRY.
IT WORKS, TYSON WINS FINAL
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A SPOT
AT THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL!
TYSON, COME ON OVER.
WHEN YOU NEEDED IT MOST.
TYSON SAFE AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU ARE
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE
FINAL THREE.
THE QUESTION IS WHO WILL
JOIN YOU AT THAT FINAL
DVYm8Q(.t THE EIGHTH AND FINAL
MEMBER OF THAT JURY.
THAT'S WHAT IS GOING TO BE
FIGURED OUT THIS AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK
TO COMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> I'M BUMMED, OF COURSE.
BECAUSE I REALLY WOULD HAVE
LOVED TO HAVE WON THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I CAN
PRESENT MONICA WITH THE
OPPORTUNITY TO DO A 2-2
VOTE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A BIG MOVE.
AND SHE'S NOT MADE A BIG
MOVE.
AND SO GO OUT WITH BOTH GUNS
BLAZING.
>> IT'S NICE TO SEE A
LITTLE BIT OF CELEBRATION
OUT OF YOU.
>> YEAH!
>> IT WAS EITHER THAT OR SIT
DOWN AND CRY.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I'VE
MADE IT TO DAY 39.
AND I HAVE A LOT OF BEST
DAYS IN MY LIFE.
WINNING THE CHALLENGE TODAY
IS PROBABLY PRETTY CLOSE.
SO WE'LL SEE IF I CAN TOP IT
TOMORROW BY GIVING A SPEECH
SO AWESOME THAT I WIN A
MILLION DOLLARS.
BUT FOR RIGHT NOW THIS IS
THE BEST DAY IN MY LIFE.
>> YOU LIKE WHEN I BOXED YOU
OUT.
>> I FIGURED THAT CULPEPPER
HAD A LITTLE DIRTY MOVE IN
HIM.
THAT IS THE TIME WE SAW
SOMETHING OUT OF YOU.
>> OF COURSE, GIVE YOU A
LITTLE ELBOW.
>> I'M STEPS BEHIND AND I'M
LIKE --
>> I EASED ON OVER TO THE
LEFT.
>> NICE.
>> YEAH, GERVASE.
>> I WAS A LITTLE BUMMED BY
NOT WINNING BUT EVEN MORE
BUMMED BECAUSE MONICA
CHECKED ME.
AND I'M LIKE ARE YOU KIDDING
ME?
WE HAVE THE SAME GOAL HERE.
TO NOT LET TINA WIN, NOT ME.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE THAT WE
DID IT?
>> I CAN NOWS THAT IT'S
DONE.
I CAN NOW.
>> IT IS REAL SIMPLE TONIGHT,
THREE VOTES FOR TINA, SHE
GOES HOME.
SO NOW IT'S EVERY MAN AND
WOMAN FOR THEMSELVES.
AND I HAVE TO CONVINCE THE
JURY WHY I'M THE BEST PLAYER
IN THE GAME.
>> I HONESTLY DID THINK THAT
I COULD GET FAR IF THE GAME.
NOT SOME OF BY WINNING IT
BUT I FELT LIKE I COULD GET
AT LEAST 30 DAYS IN.
AND THAT WAS ALWAYS MY GOAL.
>> WAS YOUR THOUGHT THE WAY
YOU WERE GOING TO GET THERE
WAS BY JUST DOING YOU,
BECAUSE YOU'RE A LIKABLE
PERSON.
>> THAT'S ALL I CAN DO.
>> THAT'S WHY IT IS SO FUNNY
HEARING THAT I'M A VILLAIN.
I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
VILLAINOUS.
YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T BEEN IN
MEAN OR NASTY INTENTIONALLY
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
>> GERVASE IS PLAYING REALLY
HARD FOR THAT JURY VOTE.
SO I NEED TO BE ON MY A GAME
FOR TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
MAYBE IT'S GERVASE'S TURN TO
HAVE HIS NAME WRITTEN DOWN.
>> WHEN TYSON PLAYED THAT
IDOL I WAS FURIOUS.
AND THE FACT THAT THEY KEPT
THAT SECRET, I COULD MAKE A
GAME CHANGING MOVE RIGHT
NOW.
AND I COULD SAY TO HECK WITH
YOU GUYS, HOW DARE YOU NOT
FILL ME IN.
>> DO YOU THINK MONICA IS
GOING TO GET ANY VOTES,
DUDE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> SHE MIGHT.
>> I KNOW.
>> WHAT IF SHE BEATS US.
DO YOU THINK THERE'S A
CHANCE THAT THAT COULD
HAPPEN?
>> YUP.
IT'S CROSSED MY MIND.
>> YEAH, MINE TOO.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
TONIGHT?
>> WELL, MY ONLY PLAY AT
THIS POINT WOULD BE IF YOU
WOULD AGREE TO GO WITH ME
AND VOTE VER GAES.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND BECAUSE YOU KNOW THAT
TYSON AND GERVASE WOULD VOTE
ME.
>> CORRECT.
>> AND SO YOU KNOW THAT
WOULD PUT US AT A TIE WHICH
WOULD END UP MAKING ME AND
GERVASE BUILD A FIRE AND COY
BEAT GERVAIS IN A FIRE.
>> I KNOW THAT --
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW UP SET
YOU ARE ABOUT ANYTHING THAT
HE MIGHT HAVE SAID ABOUT YOU
OR YOU KNOW, HIM
ACKNOWLEDGING THE THING THAT
HE'S-- THAT'S MY ONLY PLAY.
AND YOU KNOW, I KNOW YOU'VE
GOT TO DO WAS'S RIGHT FOR
YOU.
BUT THAT'S MY PLEA TO YOU.
>> THE ONLY WAY THAT I COULD
STAY INTO THIS GAME WOULD BE
IF MONICA HAD SOME SORT OF
ANIMOSITY TOWARDS GERVASE.
AND THEN SHE AND I COULD
VOTE FOR GERVASE TO DO A 2-2
VOTE.
AND LET IT GO TO FIRE.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK GERVASE'S
CHANCES ARE OF WINNING THIS
GAME?
>> I HEAR WHAT YOU ARE
SAYING, I HEAR WHAT YOU ARE
SAYING.
>> HE PLAYED A BETTER SOCIAL
GAME.
I THINK MORE PEOPLE LIKE
GERVAIS THAN TYSON, FOR SOME
REASON.
>> UH-HUH.
>> SO I THINK HE'S GOT A
BETTER SHOT.
>> RIGHT, THAT HE'S PERHAPS
UNBEATABLE.
>> THE MAJOR DILEMMA IS TO
MAKE GERVASE BUILD FIRE,
GOOD, I MAKE A BIG MOVE,
THAT'S A HUGE STRATEGIC MOVE,
AND YOU KNOW, GERVASE HAS
BEEN TALKING SMACK ABOUT ME.
PUT HIS FEET TO THE FIRE,
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY, EARN YOUR
SPOT IN THE FINAL THREE.
>> GET RID OF GERVAIS-- GERVASE,
THAN ME, YOU, TYSON.
>> THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
>> BECAUSE IT ALSO GIVES ME
BENEFIT OF ANOTHER BIG MOVE
IN FRONT OF THE JURY.
I'M SMACKING GERVASE BACK,
BIG MOVE IN FRONT OF THE
JURY, BUT HERE IS THE
DILEMMA.
WHAT IF TINA WON, WOULD I
WANT TO SIT NEXT TO TINA?
>> NOW BRING IN THE MEMBERS
OF OUR JURY.
ARAS, VYTAS, CALEB, KATIE,
HAYDEN, LAURA AND CIERA.
SO THIS IS IT.
SURVIVE TONIGHT'S TRIBAL YOU
MAKE IT TO THE END.
TINA, DID YOU FEEL THE
PRESSURE BASED ON THE LAST
TRIBAL THAT YOU HAD TO WIN
TODAY?
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
I KNEW I HAD TWO CHANCES
TODAY.
ONE WAS TO WIN THE
CHALLENGE.
AND WHEN GRAHNIE DIDN'T PULL
THAT OFF.
I HAD TO GO TO PLAN B.
>> Jeff: PLAN B IS WORK
MONICA.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: MONDAY CA, AT THE
LAST TROOIBAL YOU WERE VERY
CLEAR THAT IS TO THE ABOUT
AN ALLIANCE, IT'S ABOUT ME
INWINNING THIS GAME.
IT WAS VERY CLEAR AT TODAY'S
CHALLENGE TO ME THAT THIS
ALLIANCE WAS OVER WHEN YOU
CHECKED GERVASE AS HE TRIED
TO PASS YOU COMING UP THE
STAIRS.
>> WELL, GERVAIS-- GERVASE
HAS ADMITTED TO TALKING
SMACK.
AND 43-YEAR-OLD SCRAPPY
MONICA IS GOING TO HIP BUMP
YOU BACK.
>> Jeff: GERVASE, DID@vxe THAT
MOVE SURPRISE YOU?
BECAUSE IT REALLY WASN'T
IMPORTANT IN THE CHALLENGE.
IT WAS MORE OF A SIGNAL LIKE,
STEP BACK.
>> YEAH, I WAS REAL
SURPRISED.
SHE HAD A GOOD LEAD ON ME
BUT I CLOSED THE GAP QUICK
AND I WANTED TO LET HER KNOW
HEY I'M COMING ON YOUR LEFT,.
>> Jeff: YOU EVEN SAID THAT.
>> SO SHE SLOWED UP, PUT HER
ELBOW UP AND HIT ME INTO THE
RAIL.
I WAS SHOCKED.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A
CONTINUATION OF THE
STATEMENT YOU MADE AT THE
LAST TRIBAL.
ALL BETS ARE OFF, I'M HERE
TO WIN.
>> NO QUESTION.
THE LAST THREE TRIBAL
COUNCILS I'VE BEEN IN POLL
POSITION.
EVEN TODAY HISTORICALLY THE
PERSON THAT WINCE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY IS KING FOR THE DAY
AND EVERYBODY'S LOBBYING WHY
HE SHOULD TAKE ME.
>> Jeff: THAT WASN'T THE
CASE TODAY.
>> NO, TINA CAME TO ME AND
SAID WE CAN'T VOTE TYSON, WE
CAN ONLY VOTE GERVASE.
AND I WOULD LOVE TO MAKE
FIRE AGAINST GERVASE
TONIGHT.
ARE YOU IN, WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
>> Jeff: TINA, WHAT WOULD BE
IN THAT FOR MONICA?
>> WELL, EVERY PERSON
SITTING HERE IS TRYING TO
GET TO THE END.
AND YOU'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
WHO DO YOU WANT TO GET TO
THE END WITH.
>> Jeff: GERVASE, WHEN YOU
SEE TINA WORKING MONICA AND
YOU KNOW I'M THE ONE THEY'RE
GOING TO BE GUNNING FOR,
DOES THAT CONCERN YOU A
LITTLE BIT IF.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND THE CLOSER THE GAME GETS
TO THE END YOU THINK, I'M
HERE.
BUT IT'S SO MUCH WORK TO
STILL DO.
>> Jeff: IS THERE STILL A
FEELING, GERVASE, THAT A BIG
MOVE EVEN TONIGHT COULD HELP
SWAY A JURY TOMORROW?
>> YES, BIG MOVE SWAYS A LOT
OF PEOPLE IT MAKES PEOPLE
STAND UP AND SAY, WOW, THAT
WAS GREAT.
SO BIG MOVES ARE SCARY IN
THIS GAME.
AND THEY COULD HAPPEN AT ANY
TIME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS
TIME TO VOTE.
TYSON, YOU'RE UP
.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, TINA.
TINA.
GERVASE.
TWO VOTES TINA, ONE VOTE
ONE VOTE LEFT.
16th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE 8th AND FINAL MEMBER OF
OUR JURY, TINA.
NEED TO BRING YOUR TORCH.
>> YOU GUYS BE KIND TO ONE
ANOTHER TOMORROW, OKAY?
>> I'LL TRY.
>> Jeff: TINA, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
TYSON, MONICA, GERVASE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'VE GONE AS FAR AS YOU
CAN GO IN THIS GAME.
THE POWER NOW SHIFTS TO THE
JURY.
EIGHT PEOPLE VOTED OUT NOW
HOLD YOUR FATE IN THEIR
HANDS.
THEY WILL DECIDE WHO THEY
THINK IS WORTHY OF THE TITLE
OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE
MILLION DOLLAR CHECK THAT
GOES ALONG WITH IT.
YOUR JOB, CONVINCE THEM.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE NIGHT OUT
HERE.
GET SOME SLEEP, START
WORKING ON YOUR SPEECH.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> OH MY GOODNESS.
I THINK THIS IS SO HARD FOR
ME, MAINLY BECAUSE I KNOW I
WAS ONE TRIBAL COUNCIL FROM
TYING SANDRA'S RECORD OF
HAVING TWO WINS.
BECAUSE I KNOW IF THEY HAD
KEPT ME, IF I HAD TO BUILD A
FIRE AGAINST GERVAIS VAES I
WOULD HAVE WON.
SO THAT'S KIND OF HARD.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME
SURVIVOR NEVER CEASES TO
DELIVER AN ADVENTURE OF A
LIFETIME.
>> WE DID IT, WE DID IT, WE
DID IT.
>> WE DID IT.
>> SURE DID.
>> I SEE CHILLING CHAMPAGNE.
WOW.
AND ICE.
>> MANGOS.
>> LET'S GO.
>> THIS MORNING, ME, MONICA,
GERVASE WOKE UP, THE
BREAKFAST I'VE BEEN DREAMING
OF SINCE DAY ONE AND EVEN
BEFORE THAT DAY WAS THERE
AND READY FOR CONSUMPTION.
>> 39 DAYS.
>> TO GOOD FRIENDS, TO THE
REST OF OUR LIVES.
>> THERE WERE SO MANY
MOMENTS ALONG THE WAY WHERE
I THOUGHT I'M TO THE GOING
TO DO THIS.
I'M TO THE GOING TO GET TO
DAY 39.
BUT WITH SIX PEOPLE LEFT IN
THE GAME, FIVE PEOPLE LEFT
IN THE GAME, I THOUGHT THIS
IS GOING TO ACTUALLY HAPPEN.
I'M GOING TO FIND MYSELF IN
THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND NOW I HAVE TO FOCUS ON
WINNING A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> IT'S JUST AMAZING, THE
FINAL THREE.
AND MONICA DID IT WITHOUT
BRAD.
AND WITHOUT HER SAFETY NET.
AND WITHOUT ANYBODY ELSE.
AND THE-- AND THE MOM FOUND
HERSELFS AN BECAME MONICA
AGAIN.
AND IF ALL GOES WELL TONIGHT,
I COULD WALK AWAY AS THE
SOLE SURVIVOR IN THIS FIRST
HISTORIC SEASON OF BLOOD
VERSE WATER.
>> A LOT OF BLOOD, SWEAT AND
TEARS WENT TO GET ME TO
WHERE I NEEDED TO GET IN
THIS GAME AND IT'S ALL WORTH
IT.
I HAVE COME FULL CIRCLE.
I'M ONE OF THE ORIGINAL
PLAYERS TO EVER PLAY THIS
GAME.
AND AFTER 13 YEARS I COME
BACK TO A GAME THAT IS
TOTALLY DIFFERENT THAN THE
WAY I LEFT IT.
AND I ENDED UP IN THE
FINALS.
THAT'S NOT LUCK.
THAT'S NOT CHANCE.
THAT'S BECAUSE I KNOW HOW TO
PLAY THIS GAME.
SO I'M FEELING GOOD HEADING
INTO THIS FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
I THINK I REALLY DO HAVE A
GOOD SHOT AT WINNING THIS
MILLION DOLLARS AND
CONVINCING THIS JURY THAT I
AM THE SOLE SURVIVOR
WE NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY, ARAS,
VYTAS, CALEB, KATIE, HAYDEN,
LAURA, CIERA AND TINA.
WELCOME TO YOUR FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
39 DAYS.
IT'S AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO IN
THIS GAME.
NOW THE POWER IN THE GAME
SHIFTS TO THE JURY.
EIGHT PEOPLE THAT YOU HAD A
HAND IN VOTING OUT WILL NOW
DECIDE WHO GETS THE TITLE
SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE
MILLION DOLLAR CHECK THAT
GOES WITH IT.
LET'S START WITH OPENING
STATEMENTS.
YOUR FIRST CHANCE TO ADDRESS
THEM ABOUT WHY YOU DESERVE
TO WIN THIS GAME.
THEN THEY'LL GET THEIR
CHANCE TO ADDRESS YOU.
THEN WE VOTE.
GERVASE, YOU'RE UP FIRST.
>> HOW'S IT GOING, JURY.
I THINK THAT I PLAYED THIS
GAME GREAT.
I USED THE BEST OF OLD
SCHOOL AND NEW SCHOOL
SURVIVOR.
I HAD A 13 YEAR LAYOFF, CAME
BACK INTO THIS GAME.
YOU TAKE ANY ATHLETE IN ANY
SPORT, THE ROOKIE SEASON,
GIVE THEM 13 YEARS OFF, THEY
WILL NOT MAKE IT TO THE
FINALS.
NEW SCHOOL STRATEGY, I'VE
DONE THE BIG BLINDSIDES,
STARTED WITH ARAS, YOU KNOW,
HE WOULD NEVER HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO GET OUT OF THIS GAME
IF IT WASN'T FOR ME.
TYSON WASN'T CLOSE ENOUGH TO
MAKE THAT HAPPEN IT WAS A
TOUGH, LONG HARD ROAD BUT I
PLAYED THE GAME THE WAY THE
GAME SHOULD BE PLAYED.
I THINK SIT UNTIL THIS
POSITION DEFINITELY WARRANTS
YOUR VOTES TO BE THE SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE WINNER OF
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: MONICA.
>> WELL, I JUST WANTED TO
START WITH ADDRESSING THE
ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM.
AND THAT IS I KNOW THAT YOU
ALL THINK THAT I WAS DRUG
ALONG LIKE A PUPPY DOG ON A
LEEFERB LEASH BY THESE GUYS
TO GET TO THE END.
AND THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I HAD THREE CHOICES IN THE
LAST THREE TRIBAL COUNCILS
TO GO WITH KATIE, CIERA,
HAYDEN AND TINA.
AND I NEVER CHOOSE THAT
PATH.
BECAUSE I WANTED TO FIT IN
THE END WITH THESE GUYS,
BECAUSE I HAVE LESS BLOOD ON
MY HANDS AND LESS BROKEN
PROMISES.
AND IF I WOULD HAVE SAT WITH
HAYDEN, KATIE, CIERA OR TINA,
I WOULD HAVE BEEN MORE LIKE
YOU.
AND SO MY STRATEGIC PLAY
GAVE ME THE BEST CHANCE TO
WIN.
I HOPE THAT THAT FINDS SOME
MERIT IN YOUR VOTE.
AND I AM PROUD OF THE SOCIAL
MANEUVERING AND THINGS THAT
I'VE DONE TO GET HERE.
>> Jeff: TYSON.
>> I CAME INTO THIS GAME
KNOWING I WOULD PROBABLY BE
TARGET NUMBERO UNO FROM THE
GET-GO AND MOST OF YOU
CONFIRMED THAT AS I HIT THE
GALANG BEACH.
AND SO I SAID I'M JUST GOING
TO HAVE MAXIMUM AMOUNTS OF
FUN, NO REGRETS.
AN WHEN I GET VOTED OUT, I'M
GOING TO GET VOTED OUT.
THAT CHANGED THE SECOND I
SAW RACHEL AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
WHEN SHE LEFT I SAID I HAVE
TO GET TO DAY 39, NO MATTER
WHAT IT TAKES, I HAVE TO
FOCUS EVERY DAY AND SHOW HER
THAT I APPRECIATED HER
SACRIFICE, KNOWING THAT THE
REASON SHE LEFT WAS BECAUSE
OF ME, BECAUSE HALF OF YOU
THOUGHT I WAS TOO BIG OF A
THREAT SO YOU VOTED HER OUT.
SO I DID WHAT I HAD TO.
I MADE THE HUGE MOVES.
I DUG AROUND FOR THE IDOL,
TO MAKE SURE NOBODY ELSE HAD
THEM.
AND I WON CHALLENGES WHEN I
ABSOLUTELY HAD TO.
EVERYTHING I DID WAS
STRATEGIC, NOTHING WAS OUT
OF MALICE.
AND I'M HERE, DAY 39 BECAUSE
RACHEL MADE THAT SACRIFICE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY,
SOME OF YOU HAVE WAITED
QUITE A FEW DAYS FOR YOUR
CHANCE TO ADDRESS THE FINAL
THREE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO FIRM UP WHAT YOU
WANT TO SAY OR ASK, AND
WE'LL GET INTO IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY
THIS IS YOUR FIRST CHANCE TO
ADDRESS TYSON, MONICA AND
GERVASE.
YOUR JOB IS TO ELICIT THE
INFORMATION YOU NEED TO MAKE
A MILLION DOLLAR VOTE.
LET'S GET INTO IT.
VYTAS.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOOK, GUYS,
TYSON, THE NAME OF THE GAME
IS TO GET BEFORE YOU GET
GOT.
AND YOU DEFINITELY DID THAT,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, I WASN'T
GOING TO TAKE YOU TO THE
END.
ARAS WASN'T GOING TO TAKE
YOU TO THE END.
THAT IS THE POINT YOU MADE
TO GET US BEFORE WE GOT YOU.
THE PROBLEM IS MY LAST PLAY
WAS TELLING YOU IF YOU GET
ME OUT, I PROMISE YOU I'M TO
THE GOING TO GIVE YOU MY
JURY VOTE, DOW REMEMBER
THAT.
>> I DO REMEMBER THAT I
REMEMBER YOU THREATENING
THAT.
>> THAT WAS PIE LAST PLAY,
MY LAST GROUND TO STAND ON.
AND TO BE HONEST, I'M GOING
TO STICK TO THAT.
WHICH BRINGS ME TO THE TWO
OF YOU.
GERVASE, OLD SCHOOL JUST
MEANS AN UNWILLINGNESS
TO ADAPT.
THIS GAME IS ABOUT
ADAPTABILITY AND CHANGE AND
IT HAS MORPHED IN THE 13
YEARS TO PLAY, OLD SCHOOL
WORKS FOR FASHION AND WORKS
FOR MUSIC SOMETIMES BUT IT
DOESN'T WORK IN SURVIVOR.
YOU LINKED UP WITH A NEW
SCHOOL PLAYER.
IN MY OPINION HE KIND OF
CARRIED YOU THROUGH, SO I
DON'T NEED TO YOU SAY
ANYTHING RIGHT NOW.
AND THEN WITH MONICA, WHO
WHEN THAT TRIBE SWAP
HAPPENED, THERE WAS A
GENUINE FRIENDSHIP WE HAD.
AND I TOTALLY TRUSD NEW THAT
SENSE.
THESE GUYS NEVER PROMISED ME
SOMETHING.
THEY PROMISED MY BROTHER
SOMETHING, BUT ARE YOU THE
ONLY ONE HERE THAT TURNED ON
ME.
LIKE YOU AN I HAD A
FRIENDSHIP AND YOU NEVER
CAME AND TALKED TO ME ABOUT
THAT AND HONORED THAT
FRIENDSHIP AM.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHO TO VOTE
FOR.
I'M JUST GOING TO BE
WATCHING WHAT GOES DOWN AS
THESE OTHER GUYS ASK YOU
QUESTIONS TONIGHT AND HOW IT
GOES.
>> THANKS, VYTAS.
>> Jeff: KATIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> HI.
I WANT TO SAY
CONGRATULATIONS TO EACH AND
EVERY ONE OF YOU.
I HAVE ONE QUESTION FOR
TYSON.
IN YOUR OPENING SPEECH YOU
SAID YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
OUT OF MALICE.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL WHEN WE
ALL DREW BETWEEN ME AND
CIERA IT WAS ONE OF THE
LOWEST MOMENTS FOR ME WHEN I
HELD OUT THE WHITE ROCK AND
I SAW YOU STAND UP TO HUG
ME.
BUT THEN YOU LOOKED AT ME IN
THE EYES AND YOU SAID, YOU
SEE THAT JURY SEAT OVER
THERE, THAT'S YOURS.
AND DID YOU IT OUT OF
MALICE.
>> YEAH, THAT WAS THE ONE
THING I REGRETTED DOING IN
THE GAME.
I WAS HOPING TO HAVE THE
CHANCE TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU
FOR THAT.
>> I MEAN IF YOU WERE IN MY
SHOES, WOULD YOU VOTE FOR
TYSON AFTER A STATEMENT LIKE
THAT?
>> IT'S HARD BECAUSE I KNEW
YOU WERE BEGIN GUNNING FOR
ME.
THE DRAWING ROCK THING WAS A
REAL STUFF SPOT FOR ME.
MY HEART WAS BEATING.
COY HEAR IT IN MY FACE, AND
WITH ME SOMETIMES MY MOUTH
TAKES OVER BEFORE MY BRAIN
CAN STOP IT AND SAYS THAT'S
KATIE.
I WOULD HOPE YOU COULD LOOK
PAST IT AND I WOULD HOPE
THAT I WOULD BE A BIG ENOUGH
PERSON TO LOOK PAST IT AND
VOTE FOR THE PERSON THAT YOU
FEEL PLAYED THE BEST GAME.
I WOULD HOPE COY DO THAT,
BUT I CAN'T TELL YOU WITH
CERTAINTY THAT I WOULD.
>> THANKS KATIE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AND SORRY ABOUT THAT,
KATIE, I REALLY AM, IT IS MY
ONE REGRET OF THE GAME.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: CALEB, YOU'RE UP.
>> HI, Y'ALL.
MY QUESTION IS TO YOU,
GERVASE.
WHAT WAS YOUR BIG
GAME-CHANGING MOVE?
>> I THINK MY BIGGEST MOVE
OF THE GAME WAS VOTING OUT
ARAS.
I KNOW EVERYBODY THINKS
TYSON MAKES THE MOVE BUT
HERE IS THE THING WITH MY
PLAYING STYLE.
I WAS NEVER THE TARGET.
YES, I WANTED TYSON'S TEAM
LIKE HE WAS PULLING THE
TRIGGER AND ALL THESE MOVES
BECAUSE THEY WANTED TO VOTE
OUT WHO, TYSON.
I THINK THAT'S GENIUS.
HE'S TAKING ALL THE HEAT.
BUT A LOT OF THE MOVES THAT
HAPPENED IN THIS GAME CAME
FROM ME.
>> I APPRECIATE IT.
MONICA, FOR ME, I FEEL LIKE
YOU JUST HAVE THAT PERFECT
PERSONA ABOUT YOU AND YOU
KNOW, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
HAVE SOMETHING FROM YOU.
BE VULNERABLE.
TELL ME SOMETHING INSTEAD OF
FROM UP HERE I NEED YOU TO
ANSWER FROM IN HERE.
YOU KNOW, LIKE FROM THE
HEART.
>> MY WHOLE LIFE HAS BEEN
ABOUT BRAD, AND NINE YEARS
IN THE NFL.
AND I WANT THIS.
IT'S NEVER, EVER, EVER IN
THE LAST 21 YEARS, ONE DAY,
BEEN ABOUT ME.
AND TODAY IT IS.
AND I'M PROUD OF ME.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU ALL ARE
PROUD OF ME OR NOT.
I HAVEN'T HAD A FRIEND OUT
HERE.
I FELT LIKE I'VE BEEN THE
LONELY HEART FROM THE MINUTE
BRAD WALKED OUT THAT DOOR.
AND I STAYED.
AND I FOUGHT.
AND I SAID WHAT IS YOUR GOAL
HERE, WOMAN.
AND IT IS TO GET TO THE END.
AND IT'S NOT TO JUST GET TO
THE END, IT'S TO GET TO THE
END AND WIN AND HAVE SOME
SORT OF BADGE OF HONOR FOR
MONICA, ME, OTHER THAN
BRAD'S WIFE, AND HONOR'S
MOM.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
>> I APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD LUCK, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: THANKS, CALEB.
I CIERA, YOU'RE UP.
>> HI, GUYS.
TYSON, I OBVIOUSLY TITLED
YOU THE VILLAIN.
SO I WANT TO KNOW DO YOU SEE
YOURSELF AS THE VILLAIN OR
AS THE HERO.
>> I HONESTLY DON'T SEE
MYSELF AS THE VILLAIN.
LIKE I SAID IN MY OPENING
STATEMENT, EVERY MOVE I MADE
WAS STRATEGIC.
IT WASN'T EVER PERSONAL.
IT WASN'T EVER OUT OF
DISLIKE FOR ANYONE.
EVERYTHING CAME DOWN TO HOW
MANY NUMBERS DOES THIS
PERSON HAVE, WHERE DO THEY
FIT IN THEIR ALLIANCE,
WHOSE'S THE STRONGEST
SOCIALLY, IS SOMEBODY GOING
TO BEAT ME IN A CHALLENGE
DOWN THE ROAD.
EVERYTHING I DID WAS PURE
STRATEGY.
AND FOR THAT REASON, I WOULD
SAY I'M DEFINITELY NOT THE
VILLAIN.
A HERO, RACHEL CONSIDERS ME
A HERO.
AND I GUESS FUR'S NOT THE
VILLAIN THAN YOU HAVE TO BE
THE HERO.
>> OKAY, THANKS, TYSON.
GERVASE, WERE YOU EVER GOING
TO VOTE OUT TYSON?
>> MY PLAN WAS TO DO IT AT
THE RIGHT TIME.
AND I WAS REALLY LOOKING AT
A FINAL FOUR SPOT TO GET RID
OF TYSON.
AT THAT TIME IN THE GAME, I
JUST FELT LIKE IF I JOINED
YOU GUYS, AND WE GOT RID OF
TYSON I ABSOLUTELY WAS GOING
TO BE NEXT TO GO.
AND MY BEST ODDS AT THAT
MOMENT IN TIME WERE TO STAY
WITH TYSON AND RIDE IT OUT.
AND IF I SAT HERE NEXT TO
HIM AND LOST, IT'S OKAY.
BECAUSE I MADE THAT
DECISION.
I FEEL LIKE I CAN DEFINITELY
BEAT TYSON AND THAT'S WHY I
DECIDED TO MAKE THAT MOVE
AND COME HERE TONIGHT.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S ALL I GOT FOR YOU
GUYS.
>> THANKS, CIERA.
>> Jeff: LAURA, YOU'RE UP.
OKAY, SO MONICA, I DON'T
KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
LET ME GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT IS HARD FOR ME
IS I CAN SOMETIMES BE REALLY
PRICKLY AND BE REALLY HARD
TO BE AROUND.
AND I NEED TO WORK ON THAT.
OKAY, THAT'S BEING
VULNERABLE AND THAT'S SAYING
OKAY, I'M GOING TO JUST
STRIP MY CLOTHES OFF.
HERE IS AN UGLYNESS ABOUT
MYSELF.
>> I THINK ALL MY UGLINESSES
HAVE BEEN SHOWN ON THIS
GAME.
>> TELL ME WHAT.
>> IF YOU ARE CLASSIC
CULPEPPER, A LOT OF TIMES I
THOUGHT YOU KNOW WHAT MONICA
YOU ARE COMPLETELY OUT OF
PLACE IN THIS GAME.
>> WHY, WHAT MAKES YOU OUT
OF PLACE.
>> PEOPLE SAY YOU ARE A
PUPPY DOG, PEOPLE SAY ARE
YOU BEING DRUG AROUND.
PEOPLE ARE MAKING FUN OF
PEOPLE SAY YOU TALK TOO
MUCH.
PEOPLE SAY THEY DON'T LIKE
YOUR STORIES.
PEOPLE SAY MONICA ONLY TELLS
STORIES ABOUT HER FAMILY
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING
INTERESTING ABOUT MONICA.
>> HOW DOES THAT NOT
DEVASTATE YOU AND BRING YOU
TO YOUR KNEES IN THIS GAME.
>> IT DID, NUMEROUS TIMES.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE GROWN OUT HERE.
AND I LET ALL OF THOSE
EMOTIONS GO AWAY.
AND I FOUGHT.
I WIN A CHALLENGE, ALL
LITTLE 100 POUNDS OF ME IS
FREAKING HE MASS YATED.
I'M EATING GRUBS, WORMS, PIG
INTESTINE AND I WEIGH HALF
AS MUCH AS THESE PEOPLE
WEIGH, WHY, CAUSE BECAUSE
IT'S MY TIME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT MORE YOU
WANT ME TO SAY.
>> LITTLE YOU ANSWERED IT
PERFECTLY WITH THAT, THOSE
LAST FEW WORDS THAT YOU SAID
THERE WAS VULNERABLE.
>> THANK YOU FOR ASKING.
>> THANKS.
>> THANK YOU, LAURA.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>> Jeff: TINA.
>> HEY, GUYS.
I WANT TO YOU GIVE ME ONE
WORD AND ONE WORD ONLY THAT
BEST DESCRIBES THE CORE OF
WHO YOU ARE.
MONICA?
>> GENEROUS.
>> GERVASE.
>> IT'S HONORABLE, THAT IS
WHAT GERVASE MEANS T MEANS
HON ORBL.
AND I AM A PERSON THAT YOUR
WORD IS YOUR BOND.
AND YOU KNOW, CALEB PROBABLY
DOESN'T THINK THAT, BUT
OUTSIDE OF THIS GAME, YES, I
THINK I'M A VERY HONORABLE
PERSON.
>> TYSON.
>> IT'S FUN-LOVING ONE WORD
OR IS THAT TWO.
>> I WILL TAKE IT.
>> OKAY OX FUN-LOVING.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: THANKS, TINA.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, YOU'RE UP.
>> TYSON, COMING TO YOU,
MAN.
DID YOU HAVE THE IDOL.
>> YES.
>> WHERE WAS IT?
>> I FOUND IT IN A BIRD'S
NEST UP IN A TREE, ONE STEP
AHEAD OF YOU AGAIN.
>> TOUCHE.
>> TOUCHE, PERFECT.
>> MONDAY CA, YOU KNOW I
LOVE YOU.
AND I LOVE BRAD.
HE'S A HUGE CHARACTER.
>> AND I MADE HIM.
>> AND I'M SURE DID YOU.
>> I MADE HIM.
>> AND I KNOW ARE YOU THE
BACKBONE OF THE HOUSE AND I
KNOW YOU'RE A GREAT MOM.
BUT THE PERCEPTION IS MAYBE
YOU'VE BEEN A LITTLE FAKE.
AND THAT'S YU GET BEAT UP
CONSTANTLY.
LIKE WE WANT TO SEE INSIDE
MONICA.
LIKE WHAT DO YOU THINK OUR
PERCEPTION OF YOU IS.
I MEAN I KNOW --
>> IT'S OBVIOUS, I HEARD IT
TIME AND TIME AGAIN.
WHAT DOW-- I DON'T REALLY
QUITE KNOW WHAT Y'ALL WANT
ME TO DO MORE THAN I'VE
DONE.
>> THE LAST THING I WANT TO
DO IS COME HERE AND BEAT YOU
UP THAT IS NOT WHAT I WANT
TO DO.
>> I FEEL LIKE SUCH A TARGET
TO EVERYONE.
HAVE Y'ALL NEVER MET A NICE
PERSON, HAVE Y'ALL NEVER MET
SOMEBODY THAT ISN'T SELFISH.
HAVE Y'ALL NEVER MET A NEAT
LADY.
I MEAN --
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE OPENED
UP AND IT'S JUST LIKE KEEP
PUNCHING HER.
WHAT IS Y'ALL'S GOAL.
>> THAT NOT THE CASE.
I JUST FEEL LIKE WE HAVEN'T
GOTTEN TO KNOW YOU.
>> WELL, MAYBE AT THE END OF
THE GAME WE CAN HAVE DINNER
AND COFFEE AND --
>> I WOULD LIKE THAT.
>> ME TOO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ARAS,
FINISH THIS UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CONGRATULATIONS, GUYS.
IT IS EXCITING TO SOAK IN
THIS MOMENT BECAUSE IN MY
OPINION THIS IS PROBABLY THE
BEST MOMENT OF THE WHOLE
EXPERIENCE, EVEN AFTER I WON
THE MILLION DOLLARS.
SO GERVASE LET ME START WITH
YOU.
PROVE TO ME YOU HAVE GAME
AWARENESS BY ASSUMING I CAN
ONLY VOTE FOR MONICA OR
TYSON.
AND FELL ME WHY I SHOULD
VOTE FOR THEM.
ONLY CHOOSE ONE, TELL ME
WHAT THEY DID AND WHY IT WAS
INSTRUMENTAL IN GETTING THEM
HERE.
>> I WOULD DEFINITELY SAY
TYSON.
HE HAD A LOT OF DIFFERENT
ELEMENTS TO HIS GAME.
COSEE TWO PEOPLE TALKING AND
GO UP TO THEM AND SAY HEY, I
DON'T KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON,
BUT I WANT IN.
YOU KNOW, HE HAD EVERYBODY
DIGGING UP THE BEACH,
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL THAT HE
HAD.
CHASING THEM ALL AROUND THE
IDOL TO MAKE SURE THEY DON'T
FIND SOMETHING THAT IS NOT
THERE I THOUGHT THAT WAS
GREAT GAME PLAY.
I MEAN YOU CAN'T KNOCK
ANYTHING ABOUT HIS GAME.
>> OKAY.
MONICA, WHO MADE THE BEST
MOVE?
AND WHO SHOULD I VOTE FOR
BETWEEN THOSE TWO BOYS.
>> HANDS DOWN YOU HAVE TO
VOTE FOR TYSON.
HE FOUND TWO HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOLS AND HE DID WIN THOSE
LAST TWO IMMUNITIES WHEN
PEOPLE COULD HAVE GOTTEN RID
OF HIM, BUT THEY COULDN'T.
I FELT LIKE HE WAS A
CHARGING HORSE FOR 39 DAYS.
>> AWESOME, THANKS, MONICA
CHARACTER, TYSON, SAME
QUESTION.
I CAN'T VOTE FOR YOU, I'M
VOTING BETWEEN GERVASE AND
MONDAY CAS, WITHOUT DO I
VOTE FOR AND WHY.
>> HONESTLY I WOULD HAVE TO
GO WITH MONICA.
WHEN WE TART STARTED AT
GALANG, WE WILL SOMETHING
PRETTY GOOD.
I SAID YOU WATCH MY BACK, I
YOU WATCH MINE.
TRIBE SPLIT, SHE KEPT HER
DISTANCE FROM GERVASE AND ME,
SHE ALWAYS WANTED PEOPLE TO
THINK SHE WAS ON THE BOTTOM
AND IT WORKED BEAUTIFULLY.
SHE WOULD GET INFORMATION
THAT WE COULDN'T GET BECAUSE
WE WERE TOO CLOSE TO EACH
OTHER IT WAS AMAZING HOW
WELL IT WORKED.
AND SO THAT I WOULD SAY WAS
HER BIG MOVE.
>> OKAY, THANKS, TYSON.
>> YUP.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> THANKS, ARAS.
>> Jeff: REALLY GOOD FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
HOPEFULLY THE ANSWERS YOU
GOT FROM TYSON, MONICA AN
GERVASE HAVE GIVEN YOU THE
INFORMATION NEED TO MAKE A
MILLION DOLLAR VOTE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO TAKE IT ALL IN AND
THEN WE WILL VOTE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, 39 DAYS
AND IT COMES DOWN TO THIS,
ONE FINAL VOTE.
TONIGHT YOU'RE VOTING FOR A
WINNER.
YOU'RE VOTING FOR EITHER
TYSON OR MONICA OR GERVASE.
YOU WHO YOU THINK MOST
DESERVES THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE MILLION
DOLLAR CHECK THAT GOES WITH
IT.
FOR THE LAST TIME, IT IS
TIME TO VOTE, ARAS YOU'RE UP
>> GO TO BUY RACHEL A
HOUSE AND MARRY HER AND MAKE
A LOT OF BABIES,
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN.
>> YOU'RE A LITTLE BIT
ANNOYING BUT YOU'RE A REAL
STRONG WOMAN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO GET THE
VOTES.
THANK YOU FOR A GREAT SEASON
OF SURVIVOR, OUR 27th SEASON,
39 DAYS IS A LONG TIME, I
KNOW YOU WANT ME TO READ
THESE VOTES RIGHT NOW.
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
WAIT UNTIL WE GET BACK TO
THE UNITED STATES.
SEE YOU THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NICE
WELCOME.
HAVE A SEAT!
THANK YOU FOR THE NICE
WELCOME WOW, IT'S A LIVELY
AUDIENCE.
FITTINGLY, IT'S BEEN A GOOD
SEASON.
HERE'S WHERE WE'RE AT.
39 DAYS IN THE PHILIPPINES.
NEW TWIST WITH BLOOD VERSUS
WATER.
A LOT OF EMOTION, A LOT OF
MEMORABLE MOMENTS.
BRINGS US TO A FINAL THREE,
TYSON, MONICA, GERVASE.
A JURY OF YOUR PEERS, THEIR
EIGHT VOTES.
ONE WINNER, A MILLION
DOLLARS AT STAKE.
THESE ARE VOTES YOU WANT TO
SEE YOUR NAME ON.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
HERE WE GO.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
FIRST VOTE, MONICA.
TYSON.
ONE VOTE MONICA, ONE VOTE
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
TWO VOTES TYSON, ONE VOTE
MONICA.
TYSON.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THAT'S THREE VOTES TYSON,
ONE VOTE MONICA.
TYSON.
FOUR VOTES TYSON, ONE VOTE
MONICA.
THE WINNER OF SURVIVOR BLOOD
VERSUS WATER, TYSON!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> Jeff: OUR 27th SEASON
SURVIVOR BLOOD VERSUS WATER
IS OVER, TYSON HAS WON.
NOW COMES THE FUN PART.
WE GET EVERYBODY BACK
TOGETHER ON ONE STAGE LIVE
AND WE HASH OUT WHAT WENT
DOWN, AND A LOT WENT DOWN.
PLUS WE'RE TAKING YOUR
TWEETS.
WE WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU
THOUGHT ABOUT THIS SEASON OF
SURVIVOR, #SURVIVOR FINALE T
IS THE "SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS.
WATER" REUNION SHOW.
WE ARE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)