>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE MERGED.
"BLOOD VERSUS WATER" HAVING A
LOVED ONE SEEMED TO BE A
BLESSING.
>> I'M SO STOKED I GET TO PLAY
WITH ARAS.
>> Jeff: BUT IT WAS TURNING
OUT TO BE A CURSE.
>> WHICH ONE OF US IS NEXT?
>> ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
>> Jeff: TYSON'S ALLIANCE HELD
ALL THE POWER AND THEY WERE
TAKING OUT ARAS' COUPLES
ALLIANCE ONE BY ONE.
TEEN ATHE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND AFTER TINA WAS VOTED OUT--
>> BYE, MOM.
>> Jeff: HER DAUGHTER KATIE
WAS LEFT ALONE ON THE BOTTOM.
LAURA AND CIERA WERE THE ONLY
LOVED ONES LEFT IN THE GAME.
EIGHT ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> SORRY, KATIE.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE LOST A GOOD ONE.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
IT WAS HORRIBLE SEEING MY MOM
GO.
THIS IS A CIPE OF DEFEAT, THIS
WHOLE THING RIGHT NOW.
THE SEVEN OF THEM ARE SO
ENGROSSED IN THEIR OWN ALLIANCE
THEY'RE NOT BUDGING.
FIDON'T FIGURE SOMETHING OUT
TONIGHT AND GET IT ROLLING
TOMORROW, THEN I'M DOOMED.
>> ME AND MY MOM ARE THE LAST
LOVED ONES HERE.
>> I KNOW, THAT'S SO COOL.
>> BUT A LOVED ONE IS GOING TO
BE A HUGE TARGET EVENTUALLY.
SO MOVING FORWARD IS GOING TO BE
DIFFICULT.
>> IF KATIE WINS IMMUNITY,
MONICA.
>> IF SHE DOESN'T, KATIE NEED TO
GO.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
NOW I COME HERE AND LOOK AT THE
POWER WE HAVE.
WE'RE TWO VOTES.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT WE HOLD
THE POWER IN THE GAME?
>> NO, I THINK WE'RE IN A REALLY
GOOD SPOT.
I THINK THE ONLY THING THAT
COULD MESS US UP, BECAUSE WE
HAVE THE NUMBERS, COULD JUST BE
JUST PLAYING-- LIKE LET TYSON DO
EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH.
>> JUST AVOID ANY STRATEGY
CONVERSATION WITH ANYONE,
ANYONE.
JUST STAY LOW.
SINCE I'VE BEEN PLAYING WITH MY
MOM, ONE OF THE BIGGEST THINGS
I'VE NOTICED IS A ROLE REVERSAL,
AND ESPECIALLY ONE THAT I NEVER
THOUGHT COMING INTO THIS GAME
WOULD HAPPEN.
I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW, I'LL LISTEN
TO MY MOM, DO WHAT MY MOM SAYS.
AND I THINK I'VE PROVEN TO BE
THE BETTER PLAYER.
I MEAN, I'VE HAD TO GO TO WAY
MORE TRIBAL COUNCILS THAN ON MY
MOM SO FAR AND I'VE LASTED AND
HER FIRST ONE SHE GOT VOTED OUT.
LET TYSON COME TO YOU.
BE A GIRLS' GIRL.
>> IT IS A LITTLE UNNATURAL
FEELING TO FOLLOW MY DAUGHTER'S
LEAD, BUT I TOTALLY TRUST HER
JUDGMENT AND SHE'S MY DAUGHTER.
I'M TRUSTING MY DAUGHTER'S
DISCERNMENT AND JUDGMENT, AND
THAT'S AN AMAZING GIFT THIS JOB
HAS GIVE KNOW ME.
GOOD JOB, YOU'RE DOING AWESOME.
>> I WONDER HOW LONG MY MOM WILL
KEEP LISTENING TO ME AND TAKE
MIGHT GO ADVICE.
I LOVE HER, AND I WANT TO GO AS
FAR AS I CAN WITH MY MOM.
BUT ON THE SAME HAND, IF MY MOM
NEEDS TO GO-- LET'S HEAD BACK--
IN ORDER FOR ME TO WIN THE GAME,
SHE NEEDS TO GO BECAUSE I HAVE A
BETTER SHOT OF WINNING THAN SHE
DOES.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
ARAS, HIS BROTHER, VYTAS, AND
TINA, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
DUEL?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU
WILL EACH USE A GRAPPLING HOOK
TO RETRIEVE THREE BAGS.
EACH BAG HAS A BALL SMDZ OF IT.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL THREE
BAGS, YOU WILL USE ONE OF THOSE
BECAUSE TO SOLVE THE TABLE
MAZE.
THE LOSER, OUT OF THIS GAME AND
BECOME THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER OF THIS
DUEL WILL DECIDE WHO GETS THE
CLUE TO THE LOCATION OF THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
NOW THAT IT IS AN INDIVIDUAL
GAME, THAT CLUE, THAT IDOL, A
WHOLE NEW VALUE.
TINA, DID YOU CONSIDER LETTING
KATIE SWAP SPOT WITH YOU.
>> NO WAY.
NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: I'LL LET YOU PICK
SPOTS AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
TINA HOOKS HER FIRST BAG OUT OF
THE GATE.
>> GOOD JOB, MOM, GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: VYTAS MISSES AGAIN.
ARAS HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
TINA WITH HER SECOND TOSS, JUST
MISSES.
VYTAS STRUGGLING WITH THAT ROPE.
IT'S ALL KNOTTED UP.
TINA WITH ANOTHER GOOD TOSS.
THAT WILL SNAG A SECOND BAG FOR
TINA.
>> GOOD GIRL, TINA.
>> WHAT ABOUT ME, LAURA?
>> COME ON, ARAS, GIVE IT A GOOD
SWING.
>> THANK YOU, LAURA!
>> A LOT OF SLACK.
THATTA BOY.
>> Jeff: OH, JUST MISSES!
( APPLAUSE )
, NICE!
>> Jeff: TINA WITH ANOTHERS TO
AND ANOTHER BAG.
IT ONLY TOOK HER FOUR TOSSES TO
GET THREE BAGS.
TINA NOW CAN RELEASE ONE BALL
AND START WORKING ON THAT TABLE
MAZE.
VYTAS GETS HIS FIRST BAG.
ARAS HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
VYTAS HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
IT IS THE BROTHERS NECK AND
NECK.
TINA'S ALREADY WORKING ON THE
TABLE MAZE, HAS A BIG HEAD
START.
SHE MIGHT NEED IT.
YOU DO NOT WANT TO BE LAST IN
THIS DUEL.
VYTAS HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
>> THERE YOU GO, "V."
>> Jeff: STARTED OUT SLOWLY
BUT PICKED YOU WANT PACE.
VYTAS CAN NOW START WORKING ON
THE TABLE MAZE.
>> THERE YOU GO, YOU GOT IT, YOU
GOT IT.
>> Jeff: ARAS HAS HIS BAG.
HE'S IN IT NOW.
TINA HAS HAD A BIT OF TIME TO
FIGURE THIS OUT AND ALL THREE
NOW ARE WORKING.
TWO PEOPLE ARE GOING TO MOVE ON.
TINA GETTING VERY CLOSE.
YOU CAN GET ALL THE WAY TO THE
END AND STILL DROP IN A HOLE AND
HAVE TO START OVER.
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT, MOM,
DOING GREAT, NICE AND STEADY.
>> ARAS, TAKE YOUR TIME, ARAS.
>> AH!
>> Jeff: ARAS DROPS IN A HOLE
AND HAS TO START OVER.
>> ARAS, FOCUS, MAN, COME OMAN!
>> Jeff: A HUGE TIME LOSS.
>> NICE AND STEADY.
DON'T RUSH IT.
GOOD JOB, TINA!
>> THERE YOU GO, MOM.
>> Jeff: VYTAS AND TINA AT THE
SAME SPOT ON THEIR TABLE MAZE,
BOTH VERY CLOSE TO THAT CENTER
SPOT THAT YOU WANT TO BE AT TO
WIN.
>> NICE AND STEADY.
>> Jeff: TINA DANGEROUSLY
CLOSE TO THE END.
THIS IS THE MOST DIFFICULT PART
RIGHT HERE FOR TINA.
SHE'S GOT TO GET IT THROUGH THAT
LAST LITTLE CHANNEL.
IF SHE DOES, SHE WILL LIVE TO
SEE DAY 26.
>> OH, BABY!
>> Jeff: TINA IN THE FINAL
SECTION.
NOW SHE HAS TO LAND IT IN THE
FINISH SPOT.
>> OH, NO, NO!
>> Jeff: OH, TINA DROPS IN THE
HOLE, ALL OF THAT PROGRESS LOST.
>> OH, NO!
>> Jeff: SHE MUST START OVER,
VYTAS NOW VERY CLOSE TO THAT
CENTER SECTION.
VYTAS IS NOW IN THE CENTER
SECTION.
HE'S BEEN BEHIND THIS ENTIRE
DUEL.
HE COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
HE DOES.
VYTAS WINS THE DUEL.
VYTAS STAYS ALIVE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
WE'RE NOW DOWN TO TWO.
TINA AND ARAS.
ONE WILL FAIL.
IT COMES DOWN TO THIS.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD, ARAS, TAKE
YOUR TIME, MAN.
>> NICE AND STEADY.
>> YOU HAVE PLENTY OF TIME,
TINA.
>> Jeff: TINA IS VERY CLOSE TO
THAT CENTER SECTION, BUT ARAS
KNOWS THAT MEANS NOTHING.
SHE WAS CLOSE BEFORE.
TEEN--'S NOW IN THE CENTER
SECTION.
SHE JUST NEED TO LAND THAT BALL.
ARAS TRYING TO PICK UP THE PACE.
HE'S GOT TO GET A MOVE ON, OR
ARAS WILL BE OUT OF THIS GAME.
TINA VERY CLOSE.
CAN'T GET IT IN THAT FINISH
SPOT.
TINA FINISHES!
TINA STAYS ALIVE!
ARAS OUT OF THIS GAME AFTER 25
DAYS.
SO, ARAS, I'M THINKING BACK TO
THE CHALLENGE.
IN WHICH YOU SQUARED OFF AGAINST
EACH OTHER, AND THERE'S A MOMENT
WHERE YOU SAID, "HEY, DO YOU
WANT TO STAND UP AND START
OVER?"
AND VYTAS SAID, "YES."
AND THE MINUTE YOU STOOD UP, HE
TOOK ADVANTAGE OF YOU IN THAT
MOMENT.
IS THERE ANYTHING ABOUT THIS
EXPERIENCE OUT HERE THAT MIGHT
COMPEL YOU GUYS TO LET SOME OF
THAT GO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW, JEFF.
I MEAN--
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, DO YOU SEE THE
PAIN IT CAWDS IN YOUR BROTHER?
HHE'S HAD IT HERE.
HE HAD IT BACK IN THAT CHALLENGE
WHEN HE CRIED AND SAID, "I'M
DONE COMPETING AGAINST MY
BROTHER.
I JUST WANT TO LOVE EACH OTHER."
>> THAT FIRST CHALLENGE AIR
FORCE BUNCH OF OLD ( BLEEP )
COMING UP FOR ME AND FOR HIM.
THAT CHEAP SHOT STUFF, I'LL
NEVER DO THAT AGAIN.
AND I BELIEVE WE CAN BE HEALTHY
MOVING FORWARD AS BROTHERS AND
CONTINUING TO HAVE A LITTLE BIT
OF RIVALRY, AT LEAST.
>> Jeff: HOW DOES THAT FOOL TO
YOU, ARAS?
>> I LOT OF THINGS HAPPENED FOR
A LONG TIME, AND THINGS ARE
GETTING BETTER AND BETTER EVERY
DAY, AND THIS EXPERIENCE HAS
MADE IT BETTER, AND I HOPE WE
CAN LIVE TO A RIPE, OLD AGE
TOGETHER.
AND HAVE STORIES WITH OUR
GRANDCHILDREN ABOUT THE
EXPERIENCE WE HAD OUT HERE WHEN
WE GOT BLINDED SIDED BY GERVASE.
>> AND CAN'T WAIT TO SAYER THAT
STORY WITH MY GRANDCHILDREN.
OTHER THAN, THAT I'LL REALLY
HAPPY FOR VISE.
I DIDN'T WIN A MILLION DOLLARS
BUT WE GOT A LOT CLOSER AND
THAT'S WORTH MORE THAN ANY MONEY
IN THE WORLD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ARAS,
AFTER 25 DAYS, IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO GO.
AND BECOME THE FIRST MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
DROP YOUR BUFF IN THE URN.
>> ALL RIGHT, DUTY, I LOVE YOU,
MAN HAVE FUN.
>> LOVE YOU, BRO.
>> CATCH SOME FISH.
>> EAT SOME CHEESEBURGERS FOR
ME.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> NO HARD FEELINGS, BY THE WAY,
GUYS.
YOU OUTPLAYED ME.
GOOD JOB.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, VYTAS, FOR
WINNING THIS DUEL, YOU DECIDE
WHO GET THE CLUE TO THE IDOL.
NOW THAT WE ARE MERGED, A WHOLE
DIFFERENT VALUE IN THIS GAME.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE IT TO SOMEBODY.
ONE OF THOSE EIGHT.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO GIVE IT TO?
>> WELL, JEFF, I PLAN ON WINNING
A FEW OF THESE HERE SO IT WILL
DEFINITELY BE PASS AROUND, BUTTA
THIS POINT IN THE GAME, I THINK
KATIE NEEDS IT THE MOST.
SO I'LL GIVE IT TO HER.
>> THANK YOU, VYTAS, I'M GOING
TO KEEP IT.
>> Jeff: NOT EVEN GOING TO
ENTERTAIN--
>> NOPE.
>> Jeff: THE CRAZY NOTION
OTHER PEOPLE HAVE DONE OF
THROWING IT IN THE FIRE.
>> IT'S GOING RIGHT IN HERE.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, TEEN AYOU
LIVED TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> THANKS "V."
GOOD JOB, MOM.
>> THANKS, BABY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS, GRAB
YOUR STUFF HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> I KNEW I WAS GOING TO TAKE
THE CLUE AND KEEP IT BECAUSE MY
BIGGEST CONCERN IS FINDING THAT
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL TO KEEP ME
AROUND AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
I'M NOT GOING TO GO DOWN WITHOUT
FIGHTING AS WELL, JUST LIKE MY
MOM DID.
>> KILLED IT.
>> GOOD TO REMEMBER, MY MOM IS
STILL IN IT.
>> ARAS GONE.
>> SHE DID GOOD.
>> YEAR, I'M PROUD OF HER.
I'M SO PROUD OF MY MOM TRADE AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IT WAS KIND OF INTIMIDATING
SEEING HER WITH ARAS AND VYTAS,
BUT BECAUSE THEY'RE TWO STRONG
GUYS BUT SHE DID GREAT AND I'M
THRILLED BEYOND BELIEF THAT
SHE'S STILL IN IT.
>> YOU YOU GUYS DON'T HAVE TO
FOLLOW ME.
I'M GOING TO THE BATHROOM.
>> READ YOU'RE CLUE.
>> I'M NOW SO LOW IN THIS GAME,
SO IT WORRIES ME THAT I COULD BE
GOING HOME AT ANY MINUTE.
I'M NOT IN A STRONG ALLIANCE,
BUT I HAVE SOME FRIENDS IN
REDEMPTION ISLAND, LUCKILY, AND
THEY GAVE ME THE CLUE, WHICH I
REALLY NEEDED TO ENSURE MY SPOT
HERE IN THE GAME.
"HALFWAY ON YOUR TREK TO
REFRESHMENT, A GNARLY VINE LIVES
NEAR A ROOT.
WHERE THE VINE ENTERS THE GROUND
IS WHERE YOU'LL DIG AND FIND
SOME POWERFUL LOOT."
THIS IS A GREAT CLUE, AND I
THINK I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE IT IS
ON THE WAY TO THE WATERFALL,
THERE IS A TREE THAT HAS A CRAZY
VINE, AND WE'VE NOTICED IT
BEFORE BECAUSE IT REALLY STANDS
OUT.
I THINK THIS IS IT.
I HAVE TO START DIGGING.
>> WHY DON'T WE HIDE ALL THE
SHARP TOOLS.
>> NOT A BAD IDEA.
>> LIKE THE CROW BAR AND
ANYTHING SHE CAN USE TO DIG.
>> I MEAN WE CAN'T GRAB IT FROM
HER BUT WE CAN FIND IT BEFORE--
>> ABSOLUTE, WHEN WE SEE WHERE
SHE'S DIGGING WE CAN DIG NEXT TO
IT.
>> NOW THAT KATIE HAS AN
IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE IT DOESN'T
WORRY ME AT ALL BECAUSE I
OFFICIALLY HAVE THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, AND KATIE IS
PRETTY MUCH A NONFACTOR.
THE ONLY THING I'M THINKING
ABOUT IS HOW TO MAKE MY NEXT
MOVE, AND I THINK A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE OKAY WITH MAKING
MOVES, AS LONG AS THEY'RE NOT
THE BAD GUY, SO I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO TAKE ANOTHER ONE FOR THE
TEAM AND BE THE BAD GUY AGAIN.
OKAY, I'VE GOT IT FIGURED OUT.
>> LAY IT ON ME.
>> ARE YOU READY?
>> YEAH.
>> US FOUR GUYS VOTE LAURA M.,
SO THAT SHE DOESN'T SEE IT
COMING AND SO CIERA DOESN'T HAVE
TO VOTE FOR HER MOM.
>> SPLIT UP THAT PAIR.
>> YES, AND CIERA WE CAN PULL
BACK IN BECAUSE WE SAY WE DON'T
WANT TO YOU VOTE FOR YOUR MOMMA.
THE SAFE BET IS TAKE LAURA M.
OUT BEFORE SHE GETS FURTHER IN
THE GAME AND COLLABORATES WITH
SOMEONE WITH HER DAUGHTER
BECAUSE THEN THERE ARE TWO VOTES
THAT YOU'RE WORRYING ABOUT
INSTEAD OF JUST ONE.
LAURA M. GOES, HOPEFULLY BEAT
SOME PEOPLE ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND, AND THEN CIERA'S IN WITH
US, AND THEN WE CAN DO KATIE AND
MONICA.
>> YEAH.
>> DOES THAT MAKE SENSE.
>> GOOD, RIGHT.
>> YEAH, IT'S GOOD.
RIGHT NOW I REALLY FEEL LIKE
TYSON HAS MY BACK.
I DO.
I THINK I CAN TRUST HIM.
DO I WANT TO GET RID OF LAURA
M.?
DO WE MAKE A BIG MOVE NOW?
DO WE STICK WITH WHAT WE'VE BEEN
DOING?
IT'S NOT EASY BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TO TREAD CAREFULLY OUT HERE
BECAUSE ONE MISTAKE COULD COST
YOU A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> GOOD CHALLENGE TOMORROW.
>> YEAH.
>> WE HAVE TO WIN.
>> LAURA CAN'T WIN BECAUSE THIS
IS OUR OWN CHANCE TO GET HER
BEFORE SHE'S GOING TO START
SUSPECTING US.
>> YEAH.
>> IF WE MAKE THIS MOVE--
>> HOME FREE.
>> THEN WE'RE HOME FREE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY I'VE BEEN
WEARING MY SHIRT THIS WHOLE TIME
LIKE AN IDIOT.
THERE YOU GO, LADIES.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I LIKE LAURA.
SHE LOVES MY JOKES.
KATIE IS JUST SO-SO ON MOST OF
THEM.
>> I'M IN THIS ALLIANCE WITH
SEVEN, BUT THERE ARE FOUR GUYS
IN OUR ALLIANCE RIGHT NOW.
IT WILL BE SO EASY FOR THEM TO
GET RID OF ME AND MY MOM.
WE'RE THE ONLY COUPLE IN THE
GROUP.
IF I GO WITH MY MOM RIGHT NOW
AND SAY LET'S TRY TO GET TO THE
END, IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
SHE'LL BE VOTED OUT, AND I'LL BE
NEXT.
AND IT'S A CONVERSATION I HAVE
TO HAVE SOON, AND IT'S SO HARD
FOR ME.
IT'S LIKE A TOTAL-- LIKE MY
HEART IS JUST BEING TUGGED
BECAUSE NOBODY WANTS TO DO THAT.
I LOVE MY MOM, AND I DON'T WANT
HER TO THINK THAT I DON'T WANT
HER TO SUCCEED IN THE GAME, BUT
I MEAN, I-- I WANT TO SUCCEED IN
THE GAME.
LET'S TAKE IT STEP PIE STEP
REALLY QUICK AND JUST THINK
THROUGH OUR OPTIONS.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'RE AT EIGHT.
>> RIGHT.
>> IF KATIE GETS AN IDOL THIS
WEEK, WHICH SHE'S EITHER GOING
TO FIND IT OR NOT.
LET'S JUST ASSUME SHE DOES.
>> OKAY.
>> THE PLAN IS MONICA.
OKAY.
AND THEN NOW IT'S DOWN TO SEVEN.
>> RIGHT.
>> IF YOU WERE NOT IN THE GAME
RIGHT NOW, I KNOW I'D BE IN THE
FINAL CIRCLE.
>> HERE'S THE DEAL-- WOULD YOU
WIN?
THEY WOULD TAKE YOU TO THE FINAL
THREE BECAUSE THEY KNOW THAT
THEY CAN BEAT YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I WOULD WIN,
BUT I THINK I HAVE A BETTER SHOT
AT WINNING THAN YOU WOULD.
IN ORDER FOR YOU TO MAKE IT TO
THE FINAL THREE, YOU WOULD HAVE
TO WIN EVERY SINGLE CHALLENGE
FROM HERE UNTIL THE END.
I'VE DEFINITELY HAD TO HAVE
CONVERSATIONS WITH MY MOM THAT
HAVE BEEN HARD IN MY LIFE, ONE
THAT COMES BACK IS WHEN I GOT
PREGNANT, HAVING TO HAVE THAT
CONVERSATION WITH MY MOM.
AND YOU LEARN YOUR MOM LOVES YOU
NO MATTER WHAT.
AND I KNOW THAT ABOUT MY MOM.
I THINK WHAT'S IMPORTANT FOR ME
IN THIS CONVERSATION IS TO BE
HONEST.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TELL HER,
LIKE, YOU DON'T STAND A SHOT.
YOU DON'T.
AND I DO.
I DON'T KNOW BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
HAD A CONVERSATION WITH THE
GUYS, BUT I CAN SEE THEM TAKING
KATIE FURTHER--
>> I DON'T THINK THEY WILL TAKE
KATIE.
>> YOU THINK THEY'RE GOING TO BE
HONEST TO THE SIX.
>> YES, I DO, I THINK THEY'RE
GOING TO BE HONEST TO THE SIX.
>> ALL I'M SAYING IS IF IT DOES
COME DOWN TO SIX, AND YOU'RE
NUMBER SIX, YOU HAVE TO GO.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE YOU DON'T STAND A
CHANCE.
NOBODY IS TAKING YOU.
>> OR I'M GOING TO WIN IMMUNITY.
>> AND THEN GIHOME AND YOU'D GO
HOME RIGHT AFTER ME.
YOU'D GO HOME RIGHT AFTER ME AND
NONE OF US ARE SITTING IN THE
FINAL THREE.
>> HERE'S THE OTHER THING--
>> IF WE GET TO SIX AND YOU WIN
IMMUNITY I'M GONE.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO VOTE MY
MOM OUT.
I CAME INTO THIS WANTING TO SIT
AT THE END WITH MY MOM BUT IT
JUST WON'T HAPPEN.
IT'S NOT PRACTICAL.
I GET ONE SHOT AT THIS, ONE
SHOT.
AND I DON'T WANT TO MESS IT UP.
I JUST DON'T THINK IT'S
REALISTIC FOR ME AND YOU TO BE
IN THE FINAL THREE.
I FEEL LIKE WE COULD TRY IT, BUT
I THINK IT'S RISKING EVERYTHING
IF WE TRY IT.
DO YOU SEE FOR ME THAT'S
FRUSTRATING.
I COULD VOTE YOU OUT FEDERAL AND
THEN I COULD GO ALL THE WAY TO
THREE.
>> THE AMAZING PART OF WHAT
THIS-- WHAT'S HAPPENING TO US
OUT HERE ON THE ISLAND IS OUR
RELATIONSHIP IS MORPHINE.
WE'RE ALWAYS GOING TO BE
MOTHER-DAUGHTER, ALWAYS.
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN CHANGE
THAT.
BUT IT'S MORPHING INTO A ROLE
WHERE I WAS ALWAYS THE ONE
GIVING ADVICE TO CIERA.
I WAS ALWAYS THE ONE SAYING,
"THIS IS WHAT YOU NEED TO DO.
HERE IS HOW YOU NEED TO DO IT."
AND SHE WOULD GLADLY COME TO
ME-- SOMETIMES-- AND TAKE THAT
ADVICE.
IT'S NOW MORPHED INTO ROLE WHERE
I'M TRUSTING HER DECISIONS.
>> I'M WORRIED THAT I'M GOING TO
WAIT AND EXPWAIT IT WILL BE TOO
LAST MINUTE FOR ME TO DO
ANYTHING AND IT'S JUST GOING TO
BE THE WAY IT IS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
NOT SAYING GET YOU OUT NOW.
I'M SAYING WHAT IF IT GETS TO
SIR, YOU BEAT ME IN A CHALLENGE
AND I GO HOME NAP WOULD SUCK.
>> SHE HAS THE COURAGE NOW TO
SAY TO HER MOM, "MOM, THIS IS
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO, AND THIS
IS HOW I'M GOING TO DO IT.
AND BY THE WAY, I MAY HAVE TO
VOTE YOU OUT OF THAT MILLION
DOLLARS."
AND THE FACT THAT MY DAUGHTER
HAS THE COURAGE TO SAY THAT TO
ME SHOWS THAT SHE HAS GROWN AS A
WOMAN, THAT SHE'S NO LONGER THIS
LITTLE GIRL WHICH ULTIMATELY FOR
ME-- MAKES ME PROUD BECAUSE
ULTIMATELY FOR ME, I WANTED THIS
GAME TO TEACH MY DAUGHTER HOW
STRONG SHE IS.
AND TO SIT THERE AND TO SEE HOW
STRONG SHE WAS AND TO HEAR HER
SAY, "THIS IS WHAT I'M GOING TO
DO, MOM.
YOU'RE KIND OF HINDERING ME ON
THIS AND I MIGHT HAVE TO GO OVER
YOU AS AN INDIVIDUAL PLAYER IN
THE GAME WAS LIKE, OH, NO,
THAT'S GOING TO CUT MY CHANCES.
BUT AS A MOTHER, I WAS LIKE GOOD
GIRL.
I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE WE'RE THE
LAST COUPLE?
>> I KNOW.
IT IS A HUGE BLESSING FOR ME TO
BE OUT HERE TO WITNESS THAT.
WORTH WAY MORE THAN A MILLION
DOLLARS, WORTH WAY MORE THAN A
MILLION DOLLARS.
THE LAST COUPLE OUT OF ALL THE
PEOPLE.
US TWO MORETT GIRLS.
>> MY BIGGEST CONCERN IS JUST
EITHER WINNING THE CHALLENGE OR
FINDING THAT HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, AND AS SOON AS DAY BREAKS,
I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR THAT
THING.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO START
EATING EACH OTHER EVENTUALLY.
I MEAN, THERE'S SEVEN OF THEM,
AND THEY'RE GOING TO START
FIGHTING, AND HOPEFULLY I HAVE
EITHER A NECKLACE AROUND MY NECK
OR THAT IDOL THAT WILL KEEP ME
AROUND AND I CAN GET IN A SOILED
ALLIANCE AND GO FROM THERE.
>> KATIE HAVING THE THIRD CLUE
TO THE IDOL IS A HUGE THREAT.
IF KATIE FINDS THE IDOL, IT
COULD BE ME.
BECAUSE MY NAME HAS ALREADY BEEN
WRITTEN DOWN.
I'VE ALREADY BEEN SENT TOO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
APPARENTLY, CIERA TELLS ME I'M
THE BIGGEST THREAT THAT'S ON THE
TEAM.
NOW I HAVE T TO TAIL KATIE ALL
MORNING LONG, AND TRY TO FOUND
THAT IDOL.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, I WAS FOLLOWED
BY LAURA M., AND SO I HAD TO
START DIGGING WITH HER.
>> YOU'RE GONNA WEAR YOURSELF
OUT FOR THE CHALLENGE TODAY.
>> I THINK IT WILL BE OKAY.
IT'S FRUSTRATING BUT I'M DIGGING
IN ALL THE WRONG PLACES, SO SHE
DOESN'T KNOW EXACTLY WHERE IT
IS.
>> KATIE HAD A HEAD START.
>> HOW FAR OUT WAS SHE?
>> KATIE WAS ABOUT--
>> FOUR MINUTES.
>> WAS SHE RUNNING?
>> LAURA--
>> SHE PROBABLY GOT ABOUT A
THREE-MINUTE HEAD START.
>> LAURA M., IMMUNITY IDOL
HUNTER.
( LAUGHTER )
>> RIGHT NOW, IT'S A SHIFTING
GAME, PARTLY BECAUSE PEOPLE
ASSUME THERE'S A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL OUT THERE.
ALSO, BECAUSE I'M THE BIGGEST
THREAT IN THE GAME.
I'M LIKE THE BIG, BAD WOLF
ALMOST.
PEOPLE AREN'T LIKING ME.
THEY LIKE ME JUST FINE HERE, BUT
THE SECOND I VOTE THEM OUT, THEY
HATE ME, AND SO I NEED TO GET
CIERA ON BOARD ABOUT VOTING HER
MOM OUT.
WE HAVE A GOOD RELATIONSHIP, AND
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
THAT'S GOING TO BLOW YOUR MIND A
LITTLE BIT, AND YOU'RE GOING TO
MAYBE NOT BE SUPER HAPPY.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO VOTE MY MOM.
>> I'M NOT VOTING YOUR MOM.
HADEEP AND CALEB ARE GOING TO
VOTE YOUR MOM.
>> I KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO VOTE
MY MOM, AND HERE'S THE THING,
I'M OKAY WITH VOTING MY MOM OUT.
I TOLD TYSON I WOULD BE OKAY
VOTING MY MOM OUT.
>> SKIER AI HAVE YOUR BACK, I
DO.
>> BUT HONESTLY, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO AT THERE
POINT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
KATIE, I MUST TAKE IT BACK.
>> ALL RIGHT, IT'S BEEN FUN
WHILE IT LASTED.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE STANDING ON A VERY
SMALL PLATFORM OVER THE WATER
LEANING BACK HOLDING ON TO A
ROPE.
EVERY FIVE MINUTES, YOU'LL MOVE
YOUR HANDS FURTHER DOWN THE
ROPE, MAKING IT MORE DIFFICULT
TO HANG ON.
WHEN YOU CAN'T HANG ON ANY
LONGER, YOU'LL FALL IN THE WATER
AND YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTING
OUT OF THIS TRIBE TONIGHT, SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHERE THEY
WILL HAVE TO FIGHT TO GET BACK
IN THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF TODAY'S
CHALLENGE WILL HAVE THE CHANCE
TO FILL THEIR BELLY ON
HAMBURGERS, CHEESEBURGERS, HOT
DOGS, FRENCH FRIES.
AND SODA.
I KNOW IT'S WORTH PLAYING FOR.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
GET A GOOD GRIP.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN OUT HERE FOR
26 DAYS LIVING WITH VERY LITTLE.
YOUR HANDS ARE PROBABLY BEAT UP
FROM ALL SORTS OF THINGS.
NOW YOU'LL START TO FEEL IT
QUICKLY ON YOUR GRIP.
IN YOUR BACK.
HAYDEN IS EITHER STRUGGLING OR
JUST READJUSTING, HARD TO TELL.
YOU'RE TIRED.
YOU'RE HUNGRY.
YOU DESPERATELY WANT A
CHEESEBURGER.
THE ONLY WAY TO GET IT IS TO
HANG ON LONGER THAN ANYBODY
ELSE.
HAYDEN FIGHTING TO STAY IN THIS.
HADEEP DROPS IN, COULD NOT HANG
ON ANY LONGER.
HAYDEN IS THE FIRST ONE OUT, NO
SHOT AT IMMUNITY TONIGHT.
WE ARE DOWN TO SEVEN.
CALEB DROPS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO SIX.
ALL RIGHT, GET READY TO MOVE
DOWN A LITTLE FURTHER TO THE
NEXT KNOT.
HERE WE GO.
MAKE YOUR.
MOVE.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
WE'RE DOWN TO THE NEXT SECTION
OF ROPE.
GOING IT'S GOING TO GET VERY
TOUGH NOW.
GERVASE STRUGGLING TO HANG ON.
GERVASE FALLS OUT.
CIERA FALLS OUT.
WE LOSE TWO PEOPLE.
WE HAVE FOUR PEOPLE LEFT.
KATIE, TYSON, LAURA, AND MONICA.
AND WITH THAT, KATIE IS OUT, AND
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE.
YOU WANT IMMUNITY TONIGHT!
LAURA FALLS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
TYSON AND MONICA.
TYSON STRUGGLING TO HANG ON.
TORN ROTATOR CUFF.
MONICA STARTING TO STRUGGLE NOW.
BOTH FIGHTING TO HOLD ON FOR
IMMUNITY.
TYSON STRUGGLING.
TYSON IS OUT, MONICA WINS HER
SECOND INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IN
THIS GAME!
( APPLAUSE )
MONICA, COME ON OVER.
YOUR SECOND INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
WIN.
TURN AROUND.
( APPLAUSE )
>> IT FEELS REALLY GOOD.
>> Jeff: MONICA IS SAFE AT THE
VOTE TONIGHT, CANNOT BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
WILLING GOING HOME TONIGHT.
BEFORE WE GET TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
YOU HAVE A REWARD.
LET ME SHOW IT TO YOU.
WE HAVE HOT DOGS, CHEESEBURGERS,
FRENCH FRIES, SODA, YOURS TO
ENJOY AND YOU CAN INVITE ONE
PERSON FROM THAT GROUP TO COME
OVER AND JOIN YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I'M THINKING THERE'S NO
POSSIBILITY THAT I WOULD EAT ANY
OF IT BEFORE I WOULD GIVE IT TO
THEM.
HOW ABOUT I HAVE NONE AND THEY
HAVE IT ALL.
BECAUSE IMMUNITY MEANS MORE TO
ME THAN CHEESE BURGERS AND HOT
DOGS AND COKE.
I'LL HAVE THAT WHEN I GET HOME.
>> Jeff: SO YOU WANT TO GIVE
UP ALL OF THIS FOOD.
>> ALL OF THIS, CORRECT.
>> Jeff: SEND IT OVER THERE TO
THEM.
WHICH MEANS YOU GET NOTHING.
>> YEAH.
I JUST-- THIS IS MY FAMILY OUT
HERE.
>> Jeff: CALEB, DOES THIS
SOUND LIKE A GESTURE OF GOOD
FAITH OR A POLITICAL MOVE?
>> IT MAY BE A LITTLE BIT OF
BOTH, BUT FIRST, MONICA'S A MOM,
SO I THINK IT COMES FROM THE
HEART.
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO.
MONICA, YOU'RE GOING TO GO OVER
THERE.
YOU GUYS, YOU'RE GOING TO COME
OVER HERE.
WE'RE GOING ON TO SWITCH SPOTS.
>> IS IT GOOD?
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> FEELS LIKE HEAVEN.
>> IT'S SO GOOD.
>> MONCARC I LOVE YOU.
>> THANK YOU, MONICA.
>> YOU GUYS ARE MORE THAN
WELCOME.
>> AWESOME.
>> THANK YOU, MONICA.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU GUYS ARE MORE THAN
WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> SNAKE!
>> A SNAKE?
>> WHERE?
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> OH!
>> IT CRAWLED IN THE SHELTER?
>> YEAH.
>> MY MOM IS EASILY THE BIGGEST
TARGET RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE MY MOM GO
AND THE HARD PART IS I DON'T
HAVE THE LUXURY OF TIME.
>> YOU PROMISE?
>> PINKY.
>> MONICA IS VOTING MY MOM.
GERVASE IS VOTING MY MOM AND
TYSON'S VOTING MY MOM, AND HE
WANTS ME TO VOTE MY MOM.
>> TYSON WANTS YOU TO VOTE YOUR
MOM?
>> YEAH, AND HE THINKS I BECAUSE
I TOLD HIM I WOULD.
>> I'M STILL PLAYING THE IDOL
JUST TO BE SAFE.
>> DID YOU FIND IT?
>> YEAH.
>> NO, YOU DIDN'T.
>> YEAH, I DID.
>> YEAH, WHY DO YOU SAY YOU
DIDN'T?
>> BECAUSE I YOU YOU DIDN'T.
>> HOW, BECAUSE I HAVE IT.
>> YOU FOUND IT.
>> YUP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I HAVE NEVER BEEN PUT IN THIS
SITUATION BEFORE WHERE I REALLY
HAVE TO LIE TO SOMEBODY LIKE
THAT.
BUT IT WORKED.
SHE JUST FOLDED HER CARDS RIGHT
AWAY.
I WOULD HAVE STUCK IT OUT A LOT
LONGER.
SHE WAS LIKE, WHAT?
HOW DO YOU HAVE THE IDOL?
MAN YOU STOLE IT OUT RIGHT FROM
UNDER ME.
WHERE WAS IT?"
I THOUGHT THAT WAS EASIER THAN I
THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE.
>> KATIE DOESN'T HAVE THE IDOL.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
>> KATIE TOLD ME.
SHE JUST TOLD ME THAT.
AND I BELIEVE HER.
>> SO DO YOU THINK--
>> I'M JUST WONDERING WE MIGHT
BE ABLE TO BUY OURSELVES ANOTHER
WEEK BY ME TELLING TYSON KATIE
DOESN'T HAVE THE IDOL AND
GETTING KATIE OUT.
DO YOU WANT ME TO GO TO TYSON
AND RECOMMEND KATIE?
>> YES.
>> I THOUGHT WHY NOT KATIE.
WE HAVE A GOOD SHOT, THEN.
I KNOW KATIE DOESN'T HAVE THE
IDOL AND THAT'S SOMETHING WE CAN
USE.
NOW I'M THROWING KATIE'S NAME
OUT THERE AND SEEING IF ANYBODY
WILL BITE AT THIS POINT.
>> CIERA.
TADHANA FIVE.
>> IT MIGHT BE GOING GOODTO GET
RID OF KATIE.
>> THE IDOL.
>> SHE DIDN'T HAVE IT?
>> 100%?
>> YES.
SHE TOLD ME SHE DOES NOT HAVE
IT.
WELL, I KIND OF LIED.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> SHE TOLD ME THAT SHE HAS THE
IDOL AND I GO, "NO, YOU DON'T."
SHE GOES, "YEAH, I DO."
AND I SAID, NO, YOU DON'T, YOU
CAN'T HAVE IT BECAUSE I HAVE
IT."
AND SHE SAID, "YOU FOUND IT?"
AND SHE GOT ALL QUIET.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE IT.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND IF IT MAKES ANYBODY FEEL
ANY BETTER, THEN HOW ABOUT YOU
OR WHOEVER VOTE MY MOM, AND
THAT'S ALL WE NEED IS ONE VOTE.
AND IF SHE DOES PLAY TTHEN IT'S
A TIE, AND THEN YOU CAN ALL VOTE
MY MOM.
>> IT'S UP TO EVERYBODY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT ME.
I DON'T THINK KATIE HAS THE
IDOL.
IN FACT I'M PRETTY SURE SHE
DOESN'T.
SO MAKING THE EASIER MOVE SEEMS
LIKE THE SAFER MOVE.
>> CALEB?
>> I MEAN, I'M DOWN WITH IT.
I MEAN, IT IS MORE HONORABLE.
>> MY OPTIONS ARE PRETTY MUCH
REALLY SIMPLE-- SEND MY OWN
MOTHER TO REDEMPTION ISLAND OR
STICK MY NECK TOTALLY OUT AND
RUIN ALL OF MY RELATIONSHIPS
THAT I'VE BUILT JUST TO HAVE MY
MOM GO HOME ANYWAY AND FOR ME TO
FOLLOW HER AT THE NEXT TRIBAL.
>>UN WHAT, WE COULD PLAY A GAME?
>> I'M TRYING TO DETERMINE IN MY
MIND RIGHT NOW WHERE DO I GO?
>> YOU'RE PLAYING, RIGHT?
>> SURE.
>> PICK A ROCK.
>> OKAY, SO IF YOU HAVE THE
BLACK ROCK--
>> LOOK HOW HAPPY CIERA IS.
>> SHE'S LIKE, I GOT IT!
I GOT IT!
>> IT WAS SO PERFECT, WE HAD IT
UNTIL WE TOLD CIERA WE WERE
VOTING HER MOM.
THAT WAS THE MISTAKE.
SKIER ASMARTER THAN WE THOUGHT
ORIGINALLY, IS MAKING MOVES AS
WELL.
>> LET'S DO THIS!
>> AND SO IT'S A LITTLE TRICKY
BUT IT'S GOT TO BE LAURA.
BECAUSE LETTING A COUPLE GET
FARTHER IN THE GAME IS TOO
DANGEROUS BECAUSE THEY CAN SWING
EVERYTHING WITH JUST ONE VOTE.
HEY, CIERA WAS TRYING TO SWAY
THE VOTES ON TO KATIE, BUT WE
NEED TO STICK WITH THE PLAN AND
DO LAURA.
>> OF COURSE.
>> I NEED TO GET THE VOTES BACK
ON LAURA AND GET THEM TO STICK
WITH THE PLAN AND VOTE LAURA
OUT.
>> WHO ARE WE VOTING FOR?
>> LAURA.
>> THE WHOLE TIME I'VE JUST KIND
OF BEEN LIKE, WHATEVER,
WHATEVER, THE THE WHOLE THING.
BUT I THINK KATIE NEEDS TO GO
NEXT.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE THE IDOL, AND I
THINK IF SHE KIND OF FLOATED ALL
THE WAY TO THE END, SHE'S
DANGEROUS TO BE SITTING NEXT TO.
SO I THINK KATIE NEEDS TO GO
SOONER THAN LATER.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
ARAS.
ALL RIGHT, SO, KATIE, LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, IT WAS YOU OR
YOUR MOM.
YOU SURVIVE.
YOU GO BACK TO CAMP.
DOES IT STILL FEEL LIKE IT'S GOT
TO BE ME NEXT?
>> YES, ABSOLUTELY, ANDUN, I WAS
HOPING AFTER REDEMPTION, EITHER
MY MOM OR VYTAS MADE IT THROUGH
TO GET A CLUE TO THE HIDDEN
IDOL.
I MEAN IT'S NOT A GUARANTEE BUT
AT LEAST IT'S SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: SO, CALEB, THIS IS
TRICKY NOW BECAUSE YOU HAVE THIS
ALLIANCE OF SEVEN, AND YOU HAVE
KATIE.
BUT IF SHE HAS THE IDOL,
SOMEBODY FROM YOUR GROUP GOES
HOME AND IT COULD BE YOU.
>> THERE ARE TONS OF MAYBES.
MAYBE IT'S STILL OUT THERE.
MAYBE KATIE HAS IT.
MAYBE ONE OF US HAS IT.
THERE ARE A BUNCH OF MAYBES.
YOU JUST HAVE TO PLAN AHEAD.
>> Jeff: TYSON, NOW THAT TEENA
IS GONE, THERE'S ONLY ONE PAIR
OF LOVED ONES LEFT, AND THEY ARE
BLOOD, MOTHER-DAUGHTER.
>> YEAH, THAT'S DEFINITELY
SOMETHING TO LOOK AT BECAUSE
THEY WILL PROBABLY HAVE SIMILAR
MIND AND SWING THE SAME WAY.
I MEAN, SINCE DAY ONE, WE'VE
BEEN LOOKING AT THAT, AND I
DON'T THINK IT'S CHANGED ON DAY
26.
>> Jeff: CALEB, DID YOU SENSE
ANY CONCERN FROM LAURA OR CIERA?
>> YEAH, THERE'S DEFINITELY A
LITTLE BIT OF CONCERN.
BUT YOU LOOK AT CIERA AND LAURA
DIFFERENT FROM TINA AND KATIE
BECAUSE LAURA WANTS THIS JUST AS
BAD AS CIERA DOES.
SHE'S NOT ABOUT TO LAY DOWN FOR
CIERA'S GAME.
SO THEY'RE BOTH-- THEY'RE
COMPETITORS.
THEY'RE BOTH REALLY SMART, AND
THEY'VE BOTH GOT AN EQUAL SHOT
IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, IS CALEB
SAYING HE'S LESS CONCERNED ABOUT
HAVING THESE TWO AS A PAIR
BECAUSE LAURA WOULD CUT CIERA'S
THROAT AS QUICKLY AS CIERA WOULD
CUT HER MOM'S THROAT.
>> THERE'S SOME TRUTH TO THAT.
THEY HAVE A COMPETITIVE NATURE.
LIKE, "LAURA, I'M YOUR MOTHER.
I BROUGHT YOU INTO THIS WORLD
AND I CAN SEND YOU OUT OF IT
"MENTALITY.
ABUT AT THE END OF THE DAY THEIR
BOND IS STRONGER THAN WHAT WOE
HAVE AND YOU HAVE TO TAKE THAT
INTO CONSIDERATION.
>> Jeff: LAURA, WHAT DO YOU
HAVE TO DO TO SAY STICK WITH THE
PLAN.
GET RID OF KATIE.
>> BEFORE IT WAS A LIABILITY TO
HAVE A LOVED ONE.
IT'S A HUGE ASSET RIGHT NOW.
ONE IS TWO.
YOU GET ONE OF US, YOU GET TWO
VOTES.
SO THERE'S GOING TO BE SEVEN
PEOPLE LEFT.
YOU PICK UP ANOTHER BUDDY AND
WE'RE ON TO FINAL FOUR.
>> BUT YOU WANT TO GET TO THE
FINAL TWO WITH YOUR LOVED ONE,
AND THAT'S ALSO SORT OF A THREAT
IN A WAY.
I MEAN, I WAS NERVOUS HAVING MY
MOM HERE BECAUSE EVERYONE
THOUGHT WE WANTED TO GO TO THE
FINAL TWO TOGETHER, AND SO
HAVING YOUR LOVED ONE HERE MAYBE
ISN'T THE BEST ROUTE ANYWAY.
AND--
>> BUT, JEFF, HERE'S OTHER THING
TO THINK ABOUT.
IF YOU SEND AT THIS POINT A
LOVED ONE HOME, YOU HAVE
SOMEBODY LOBBYING FOR THOSE JURY
VOTES FOR YOUR LOVED ONE.
BUT IF I'M HERE YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO HAVE THAT INFLUENCE ON THE
JURY.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE YOU'LL BE
COMPETING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND I THINK WHERE PROBLEMS COME
IN ANDS WHEN YOU GET YOUR
ALLIANCE, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
PEOPLE START BAIL EARLY.
AND THE NEXT THINGUN THE TOP
THREE ARE PEOPLE THAT WEREN'T
EVEN IN THE ALLIANCE, AND
EVERYBODY ELSE IS SITTING OVER
THERE GOING, "WHAT THE HECK DID
WE DO WRONG?"
>> Jeff: SO, CALEB, IS
TONIGHT'S VOTE GOING TO BE DO WE
STICK WITH THE PLAN AND GET RID
OF KATIE, OR DO WE TAKE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO GET RID OF THE
LAST LOVED ONE PAIR?
>> THAT IS THE BIG DECISION.
YOU THINK, WELL, DO WE TAKE OUT
THE LOVED ONE'S PAIR.
DO WE STICK WITH THE PLAN AND
KEEP OUR WORD AND GO TO THE
SEVEN?
AND THEN DUKE IT OUT AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENS?
I MEAN, YOU'VE GOT FOUR GIRLS,
FOUR GUYS.
YOU'VE GOT FOUR ORIGINAL GALANG,
FOUR ORIGINAL TADHANA.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> IT COULD SWING EITHER WAY.
>> Jeff: WELL, A LOT IS GOING
TO BE LEARNED.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KATIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LAYOFF THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LAURA.
KATIE.
LAURA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES LAURA, ONE
VOTE KATIE.
LAURA.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES LAURA.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VERSUS WATER."
LAURA, THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S
ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I'LL CAM BACK FOR YOU.
>> HAVE FUN.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> IT'S OKAY, CIERA.
>> Jeff: LAURA, FOR THE SECOND
TIME, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
ONCE AGAIN, YOU WILL HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: WELL, IN VOTING OUT
LAURA, WE NOW HAVE NO MORE PAIRS
OF LOVED ONES.
WE ARE LEFT WITH SEVEN
INDIVIDUALS FIGHTING IN A GAME
IN WHICH THERE IS ONLY ONE
WINNER.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> TYSON HAS BEEN IN CONTROL.
THE WHOLE GAME.
>> Jeff: TYSON'S BEEN RUNNING
THE SHOW.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUY THINKING?
THE FOUR OF VUS VOTES, GUY.
>> Jeff: ONE PLAN CAN TURN
EVERYTHING UPSIDE DOWN.
>> WE IT UPSET THESE VETERANS.
>> I'M HAVING A HARD TIME
DEFINING HIGHWAY I'M FEELING
ABOUT CIERA WRITING MY NAME DOWN
BECAUSE IT SUCKS THAT I'M HERE.
IT SUCKS THAT CIERA HAD TO DO
THAT.
IT SUCKS THAT SHE DID THAT.
BUT I'M NOT ABOUT TO QUIT NOW.
I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO STAY IN THE GAME AND EVEN
MORE TO FURTHER MY DAUGHTER IN
THE GAME.