>> Jeff: NIGHT IS FALLING IN
THE LOUZNONE STRAIT AS 10 PAIRS
OF CASTAWAYS ARE BEING DROPPED
OFF IN 10 SEPARATE LOCATIONS.
ONE RETURNING PLAYER AND THEIR
LOVED ONE.
WHAT THEY DON'T KNOW IS THEY
WON'T BE PLAYING TOGETHER.
THEY'LL BE COMPETING AGAINST
EACH OTHER.
GER VIS PLAYED THE VERY FIRST
SEASON WHEN HIS NIECE, MARISSA,
WAS SEVEN YEARS OLD.
>> I'M THE ORIGINAL WHO STARTED
THIS ALL.
THIS TIME I BELIEVE I CAN WIN
THIS GAME.
>> IT'S CUTE THAT HE THINKS HE'S
GOING TO WIN, AFTER 13 YEARS,
COME BACK, AND PLAY THIS GAME
AGAIN.
I'M FOCUSED ON ME WINNING THIS
GAME.
>> YOU'RE DEFINITELY DRIVEN.
YOU'RE DEFINITELY DRIVEN, BUT
YOU'RE NEW TO THE GAME.
>> Jeff: IN "SURVIVOR: ONE
WORLD," KAT'S INSTABILITY LOST
HER THE GAME.
NOW, ALONG WITH "BIG BROTHER"
WINNER AND BOYFRIEND HAYDEN,
THEY HOPE TO GO ALL THE WAY.
>> "BIG BROTHER" IS "SURVIVOR"
IN A HOUSE.
AS FAR AS TRAINING OR
PREPARATION I'M GOING TO BE MORE
PREPARED THAN ANYONE EXWB ELSE
WHO HASN'T ALREADY PLAYED THIS
GAME.
>> HAYDEN HAS WON A SHOW BEFORE.
THIS IS MY TIME.
THIS IS MY GAME.
>> THIS IS NUTS.
>> Jeff: IN "SURVIVOR: SAMOW"
LAURA WAS A MOTHER TO HER TRIBE
AND THIS TIMES NEED TO SPLIT HER
FOCUS BETWEEN HER DAUGHTER AND
GAME.
YET, SHE'S MY HEART.
AND NOTHING IS HARDER THAN
SEEING SOMEBODY THAT YOU LOVE
SUFFER.
>> Jeff: WITH 100 DAYS PLAYING
THE GAME, FAN FAVORITE RUPERT
HAS NEVER MADE IT TO THE END.
HIS WIFE, LAURA, HOPES TO BE THE
FIRST IN THE FAMILY TO WIN THIS
GAME AND EMERGE FROM THE SHADOW
OF HIS LEGACY.
>> I AM RETURNING TO "SURVIVOR"
FOR MY FOURTH TIME.
>> THIS HAS ALWAYS BEEN ABOUT
RUPERTER, AND RUPERT PLAYING
THREE TIMES, AND RUPERT, RUPERT,
RUPERT.
>> NOW IT'S TIME FOR LAURA.
>> Jeff: AFTER MAKE SOMETHING
CONTROVERSIAL STATEMENTS IN
"SURVIVOR: ONE WORLD" COLTON
LEFT WITH A MYSTERIOUS AILMENT
AND FEW FANS.
HE'S HOPING FIANCE CALEB WILL
PROVIDE HIM WITH THE MATURITY HE
NEEDS.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW PEOPLE AM
RESPOND TO ME.
LAST TIME I WAS THIS BIG BALL OF
ANGER.
MY HOPE IS TO SHOW PEOPLE A
DIFFERENT SIESTLED ME, THE NEW
COLTON.
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT COLTON'S
REPUTATION.
HE PISSED A LOT OF PEOPLE OFF.
I KNOW A DIFFERENT COLTON.
THIS IS GOING TO BE KIND OF A
REDEMPTION FOR HIM.
>> Jeff: WHEN CANDICE PLAYED
THE GAME IN "SURVIVOR:COOK
ISLANDS" SHE WAS A YOUNG MED
SCHOOL STUDENT.
NOW SHE AND HER HUSBAND, JOHN,
BOTH DOCTORS, HOME ONE CAN MAKE
IT TO THE END.
>> WE ARE TWO PEOPLE WHO ARE
VERY SUCCESSFUL.
IT COULD BE SOMETHING PEOPLE
PERCEIVE AS A THREAT.
>> BEING YOUNG AND ATHLETIC, I
THINK WE'LL HAVE BIG TARGETS ON
OUR BACK.
>> Reporter: FORMER NFL WIFE
MONICA, PLAYED THE GAME FOR
HERSELF IN "SURVIVOR: ONE
WORLD."
NOW SHE'LL SHARE THE SPOTLIGHT
WITH HER FAMOUS HUSBAND, BRAD
CULPEPPER.
>> NORMALLY IT'S I'M BRAD'S WIFE
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO "SURVIVOR,"
I'M THE WILY VETERAN.
>> I'M PLAY SECOND FID TOLL
MONICA.
>> I'M THE YOUNG ROOKIE.
>> IT'S MY TURN TO WIN AND THIS
TIME I BROUGHT SOME AMMUNITION.
>> Jeff: TINA, WINNER OF THE
"AUSTRALIAN OUTBACK" HAS
HERSITIS SET ON A SECOND TITLE
BUT HER DAUGHTER KATIE HAS PLANS
ON HER OWN.
>> I TOLD KATIE OUR LIVES
CHANGED SINCE THIS GAME BUT OUR
FAMILY IS VERY COMPETITIVE.
>> THERE IS JUST ONE WINNER AND
THERE ARE TWO OF US, AND THAT
POSES A VERY DIFFICULT
SITUATION.
I WOULD LOVE TO BEAT MY MOTHER
AT HER OWN GAME.
>> Jeff: TYSON WAS BLINDSIDED
IN "SURVIVOR" AND FAMOUSLY VOTED
HIMSELF OUT OF "HEROES AND
VILLAINS."
WITH LONGTIME GIRLFRIEND RACHEL
HE HOPES TO REDEEM HIMSELF.
>> I'VE BEEN DISAPPOINTED BY
"SURVIVOR" TWICE BUT THIS TIME I
FEEL LIKE I'M IN A PRETTY GOOD
SPOT.
IN A GAME LIKE, THIS I THINK THE
LOCHED ONES AREN'T GOING TO BE
PREPARED, AND I'M GOING TO SLIT
THEIR THROATS.
>> "SURVIVOR" WAS ALWAYS TYSON'S
THING.
I NEVER THOUGHT IN A MILLION
YEARS I'D BE OUT HERE.
WITH THE LOVED ONE'S SEASON IT'S
GOING TO BE A GAME CHANGER.
IT'S GOING TO BE CRAZY OUT HERE.
>> Jeff: HORR ATHE LIKABLE
WINNER OF "SURVIVOR: EXILE
ISLAND RETURNS TO THE GAME WITH
HIS BROTHER VYTAS.
>> HEROINE LED TO MY ARREST.
I SPENT A YEAR IN THE L.A.
COUNTY JAIL.
>> MY BROTHER WAS PRETTY ABUSIVE
WHEN WE WERE I DIDN'T THINKER.
AND THAT JUST INSPIRED ME TO
BEAT THINGS AT THINGS I COULD
BEAT HIM IN.
I DON'T KNOW IF ME GOING TO
"SURVIVOR" MADE MY BROTHER
ENVOOS, BUT I'M SURE WINNING IT
DID.
>> Jeff: THEY WILL HAVE ONE
NIGHT ALONE IN THE JUNGLE, A
CHANCE FOR THE RETURNING PLAYERS
TO PREPARE THEIR LOVED ONES FOR
WHAT AWAITS THEM.
>> OH, LOOK AT THIS.
"THE GAME HAS BEGUN."
>> "TONIGHT IS YOUR FIRST NIGHT
ON THE ISLAND."
>> "WITHOUT ANY SUPPLIES YOU
MUST RELY ON YOUR LOVED ONE FOR
PROTECTION, COMFORT, AND
SURVIVAL."
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WE'RE JUST SITTING RIGHT HERE BY
OURSELVES.
>> A NIGHT IN THE JUNGLE BY
>> WELCOME TO YOUR FIRST NIGHT
OF "SURVIVOR."
>> THIS GAME IS ON!
>> WHAT DO WE DO?
WE SHOULD START.
IT'S GETTING DARK.
>> ARE WE GOING TO SLEEP ON THIS
BEACH WITH THESE CRABS.
>> WHAT WHY YOUR SUGGESTIONS.
>> I'M FOLLOWING YURL LEAD!
YOU'RE THE VETERAN.
>> THAT WAS 13 YEARS AGO.
>> IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT WE
DON'T SLEEP ON THE GROUND.
THERE ARE SO MANY ANTS.
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO DO
SOMETHING?
>> NO, YOU'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: IT'S NOT EVEN DAY
ONE, BUT THE GAME HAS ALREADY
BEGUN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: THEY HAVE LEFT BEHIND
THE COMFORT AND SAFETY OF THEIR
NORMAL WORLD TATAKE PART IN THE
ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME.
IT'S "SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS.
WATER."
20 AMERICANS FORCED TO WORK
TOGETHER TO BUILD A NEW SOCIETY
WHILE BATTLING THE ELEMENTS AND
EACH OTHER.
>> IT IS ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT THINGS IN MY ENTIRE
LIFE TO BEAT HAYDEN MOSS.
>> Jeff: THEY MUST LEARN TO
ADAPT OR THEY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
>> SHE'S A THREAT TO ME.
AT SOME POINT IN TIME I WILL
HAVE TO GET RID OF HER.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, ONLY ONE
WILL REMAIN TO CLAIM THE
MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
>> I WANT TO WIN THAT MONEY, I
WANT TO WIN THIS GAME, AND I'M
GOING TO BEAT ARAS TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: 39 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE,
ONE SURVIVOR.
>> Jeff: GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING!
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO THE
27th SEASON OF "SURVIVOR."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT YOUR
FIRST NIGHT.
HAYDEN, YOU PLAYED ANOTHER SHOW,
"BIG BROTHER," DID VERY WELL.
HOW DID YOUR FIRST MOMENTS ON
"SURVIVOR" COMPARE TO "BIG
BROTHER."
>> IT'S HARD TO COMPARE THE COZY
COFINES OF A HOUSE TO THAT LUSH
JUNGLE KAT AND I SLEPT IN LAST
NIGHT.
>> Jeff: THE GOOD NEWS SYOU'RE
GOING TO EXPERIENCE THIS GAME
WITH YOUR LOVED ONE.
BUT YOU WILL NOT BE PLAYING WITH
THEM.
YOU WILL BE PLAYING AGAINST YOUR
LOVED ONE.
>> OH!
>> GEEZ!
>> Jeff: ANYBODY HERE WILLING
TO ADMIT THEY'RE LOOKING FORWARD
TO COMPETING AGAINST THEIR LOVED
ONE?
>> SORRY, MOM.
>> Jeff: WOW.
OVER HALF.
HAVE THEIR HANDS UP.
SO, KATIE, YOU WANT TO TAKE YOUR
MOM ON IN A GAME SHE WON.
>> I THOUGHT SHE WAS GOING TO
RAISE HER HAND, TOO.
I THOUGHT WE WERE JUST GOING TO
BE...
>> COMPETING IS GREAT.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE THE
HARDEST THING ANY OF US DO IS TO
GET TO THAT POINT WHERE THE
TRIBES COME OUT AND YOU SEE YOUR
LOVED ONE MIGHT NOT BE THERE.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE SAD FOR
ANY OF OUR LOVED ONES TO GO
HOME.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER, WHAT WOULD
THAT BE LIKE FOR YOU TO SEE
MONICA VOTED OUT?
>> I'M PULLED BOTH WAYS.
ON THE SURFACE I WANT TO BEAT
HER ON EVERY CHALLENGE WE DO.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO GET DEEP IN
MY HEART AND IF THERE'S A
CHALLENGE FOR A TARP AND IT'S
RAINING EVERY DAY AND WE'RE
GOING TO WIN AND SHE'S ON THE
OTHER TEAM, PART OF ME IS GOING
TO SAY, "GOD, I NEED HER TO HAVE
THE TARP INSTEAD OF ME.
I CAN DEAL WITH THIS STUFF."
>> YOU BETTER NOTOB MY TEAM
THINKING THAT.
YOU BETTER NOT BE ON MY TEAM
SAYING THAT.
>> ANSWERED WITH MY HEART
INSTEAD OF MY HEAD, AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN I GOT STARES AND LOOKS
FROM EVERY PERSON DOWN THE LINE.
I'M THINKING TO MYSELF, OH, MY
GOSH.
FIRST FIVE SECONDS OF THE GAME,
WAY TO GO, BRAD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SAY YOUR
GOOD-BYES.
RETURNING PLAYERS OVER HERE.
NEW PLAYERS OVER THERE.
>> MY HEART SANK BECAUSE I KNOW
COLTON WAS REALLY HOPING TO HAVE
ME WITH HIM TO KIND OF BE THAT
PROVIDER THEY AM FOR HIM.
BUT IT WAS DEFINITELY A WAKE-UP
CALL.
>> LOVE YOU, HONEY.
>> YOU'RE NOT CRYING, RIGHT?
>> IT WAS SAD.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, IT'S A
GAME.
AND I CAN PLAY IT ON MY OWN,
TOO.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE NO LONGER
SIMPLY LOVED ONES.
YOU ARE NOW COMPETITORS.
>> VYTAS AND I HAVE SUCH A
COMPETITIVE RELATIONSHIP THAT
THERE'S NO WAY IF I LOSE A
CHALLENGE TO MY BROTHER OUT HERE
THAT I'M NOT GOING TO HEAR ABOUT
IT FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, HONEY.
>> WATCHING MY WIFE WALK OVER TO
THE OTHER TRIBE, IT WAS A LITTLE
BIT OF A RELIEF, AND A LITTLE
BIT OF SADNESS AT THE SAME TIME.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY AT ALL
ABOUT WRITING MY WIFE'S NAME
DOWN.
BUT THEN I ALSO CAN'T PROTECT
HER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
RETURNING PLAYERS, YOUR NAME IS
GALANG.
NEW PLAYERS, HERE'S YOUR BUFFS.
YOUR NAME IS TADHANA.
ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S COMPLICATE
THE GAME A LITTLE MORE.
( SIGHS PRESENTLY
(.
>> Jeff: EACH TRIBE IS NOW
GOING TO VOTE SOMEONE OUT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY TAKE A
PARCHMENT AND A PEN.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, YOU LOOK
SHOCKED.
>> IT'S A LITTLE EARLY TO BE
VOTING SOMEBODY OUT, I THINK.
FIRST IMPRESSIONS ARE GOING TO
SPEAK VERY LOUDLY RIGHT HERE.
>> IN TRUE JEFF PROBST STYLE, HE
HAD TO REALLY TWIST THE KNIFE.
"OH, WE'RE GOING TO VOTE SOMEONE
OUT."
REALLY?
HI.
I'M COLTON.
REMEMBER ME?
LIKE, PROBABLY GOING TO BE THE
ONE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO THIS.
WE'LL START ON THE END.
HOLD YOUR VOTE UP.
LAURA.
RUPERT'S WIFE.
>> ALREADY.
ALREADY A TARGET.
>> NOT GOOD.
>> Jeff: AND YOU THINK YOU'RE
A TARGET BECAUSE OF YOUR
HUSBAND?
>> PROBABLY, YUP.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER.
>> Jeff: LAURA.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN?
LAURA.
>> Jeff: LAURA, WHO'S YOUR
VOTE FOR?
>> JARVIS' LOVED ONE.
>> MARISSA.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> NO, THAT'S ALL GOOD.
>> Jeff: IN THE BACK.
LAURA.
THAT IS FOUR VOTES FOR LAURA.
MARISSA CANNOT VOTE FOR HERSELF.
THAT MEANS ONE MORE VOTE FOR
LAURA AND YOU'RE OUT.
HERE IN THE FRONT.
LAURA.
THAT'S IT.
YOU HAVE ENOUGH.
TAKE A SPOT OVER HERE NEXT TO
ME.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: JUST LIKE THAT, FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THEIR TRIBE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: WATCHING MY WIFE GET
VOTED OUT OF HER TRIBE ABOUT
KILLED ME.
WHY THEY WOULD DO THAT, IT'S A
SMACK AGAINST ME.
THAT IS EVERYONE OF THOSE LITTLE
SCARED NEWBIES SAYING WE'VE GOT
TO STOP RUPERT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING TO PLAY
THE GAME TOGETHER.
>> GET THEM, HONEY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, RETURNING
PLAYERS, TIME FOR TO YOU VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT OF YOUR TRIBE.
CANDICE.
>> LAURA.
WHY LAURA?
>> ONLY BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HER.
IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL.
I'M SORRY.
>> Jeff: TYSON, HOLD IT UP.
LAURA.
TINA.
REVEAL YOUR VOTE.
>> I APPRECIATE WHAT YOU SAID.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHY I WROTE YOUR
NAME.
I JUST DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
YOU.
AND I'M SORRY.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> I GET IT.
>> Jeff: KAT, REVEAL.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER VOTE FOR
CANDICE.
COLTON. THREE VOTE FOR CANDICE.
TWO VOTES FOR LAURA.
RUPERT, WHO DID YOU VOTE FOR?
>> LAURA.
>> Jeff: LAURA.
THREE VOTES CANDICE, THREE VOTES
LAURA.
MONICA.
CANDICE.
THAT IS FOUR VOTES FOR CANDICE.
ARAS.
>> I'M A REDSKINS FAN.
>> JARVIS.
>> Jeff: CANDICE HAS FOUR
VOTES, LAURA HAS THREE,IS HAS
ONE.
>> FOR THE SAME REASON, MAYBE WE
CAN GO GET COFFEE AND KNOW EACH
OTHER ONE DAY.
>> Jeff: THAT IS FIVE VOTES
FOR CANDICE.
THAT IS ENOUGH.
CANDICE VOTED OUT OF HER TRIBE.
>> OH, MAN.
>> EVERY TIME I SAW HER NAME
COME UP, I FELT LIKE I WAS
GETTING KICKED IN THE HEAD.
I LITERALLY WANTED TO DO
EVERYTHING I COULD TO VOTE OUT
EVERY SINGLE PERSON WHO VOTE HER
NAME DOWN AND I'M NEVER GOING TO
FORGET THAT.
>> I WANTED TO PLAY WITH YOU
GUYS, BUT I GUESS THE FEELING
WASN'T MUTUAL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO, LAURA
AND CANDICE, YOU ARE VOTED OUT
OF YOUR TRIBE, BUT ARE YOU
NOT
OUT OF THIS GAME.
REDEMPTION ISLAND IS IN PLAY
THIS SEASON.
REDEMPTION ISLAND OFFERS YOU A
SECOND CHANCE IN THE GAME.
EVERY PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME WILL BE SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND, WHERE YOU WILL COMPETE
IN DUELS FOR A SHOT TO GET BACK
IN THE GAME.
YOU WILL BE THE FIRST TWO PEOPLE
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: BEFORE I SEND YOU TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND, LET'S PUT
THIS IDEA OF "BLOOD VERSUS
WATER" TOTS FIRST TEST.
RUPERT, VERY HEROIC.
LOVE YOUR WIFE.
DO ANYTHING FOR YOUR WIFE.
IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN PROVE IT
RIGHT NOW AND YOU CAN TAKE HER
SPOT.
BEFORE YOU DO IT, LET ME TELL
YOU THE CONSEQUENCES.
YOU CAN TAKE HER SPOT AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHICH MEANS
ARE YOU PUTTING HER ON YOUR
TRIBE.
YOU WILL BE AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND, HAVING TO FIGHT FOR YOUR
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
>> DON'T, RUPERT, DON'T.
>> Jeff: YOU OF YOU LOSE ONE
DUEL, YOU COULD BE OUT.
>> I PUT MYSELF IN A POSITION
WHERE I AM NOT SAFE.
IT'S KILLING ME.
BUT I WOULD RATHER HAVE MYSELF
IN THIS POSITION THAN I WOULD MY
WIFE.
LAURA DESERVES TO PLAY THE GAME.
DO YOU WANT TO GO TRY?
>> I WANT TO PLAY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> OH, GOD.
>> TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> Jeff: WOW.
I NEVER ANTICIPATED THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT, GIRL!
>> COME OGIRL!
>> COME ON!
>> REDEMPTION.
>> I WAS REALLY TICKED WHEN
RUPERT SWITCHED WITH LAURA.
I UNDERSTAND THE EMOTION BEHIND
IT, BUT WE WERE COUNTING ON
RUPERT.
RUPERT IS A FANTASTIC SHELTER
BUILDER.
HE'S A FANTASTIC FISHERMAN.
AND RIGHT OFF THE BAT, HE
WEAKENS OUR TRIBE.
>> Jeff: RUPERT, YOU
UNDERSTAND YOU HAVE NOW PUT
YOURSELF IN A SPOT WHERE YOU
HAVE TO WIN WUR YAY BACK IN THE
GAME.
>> TIME AFTER TIME AFTER TIME
AND I WILL.
>> Jeff: JOHN, YOU HAVE THE
SAME OPPORTUNITY.
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE A MOMENT AND
TALK ABOUT IT?
>> YEAH, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S UP TO YOU.
I THINK I CAN BEAT HIM.
>> YOU PROBABLY HAVE A BETTER
CHANCE THAN I DO.
>> Jeff: JOHN WHAT, DECISION
ARE YOU GOING TO MAKE?
>> WELL, JEFF, MY WIFE SAY
REALLY TOUGH WOMAN, AND I HAVE
NO DOUBT IN MY MIND THAT SHE CAN
WIN.
SO I THINK WE'RE GOING TO GIVE
HER THE OPPORTUNITY TO BEAT
RUPERT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CANDICE
COME BACK.
JOHN, TAKE A SPOT IN THE TRIBE.
>> TOUGH CHOICE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BIG MOVE
EARLY ON.
RUPERT'S PULLED HIMSELF OUT OF
THE GAME SO LAURA CAN HAVE A
SHOT.
CANDICE AND RUPERT, YOU WILL
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
YOU'LL COMPETE IN DUELS FOR A
SHOT TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
HEAD OUT.
>> LOVE YOU, HONEY.
>> LOVE YOU, TOO, BABY.
>> IN LAURA AND I'S WORLD, BLOOD
IS THICKER THAN ANYTHING.
AND LAURA AND I ARE BLOOD.
I'M MAKING IT BACK.
IF I CAN BATTLE MY ASS OFF
REDEMPTION ISLAND AND LAURA IS
STILL THERE, YOU BETTER WATCH
OUT, BECAUSE WE WILL BE ONE HELL
OF A TEAM.
>> Jeff: WATCHING CANDICE WALK
OFF LITERALLY FELT LIKE MY HEART
WAS BEING TORN OUT OF MY CHEST.
LIKE THE SECOND I-- THE SECOND I
SAW HER WALKING OFF, YOU KNOW, I
WAS LIKE THERE'S NOTHING THAT'S
GOING TO BE HARDER THAN NOT
DOING EVERYTHING I CAN TO SAVE
MY WIFE'S BUTT IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
YOU HAVE A LOT TO GET STARTED
WITH.
YOU'RE BUILDING A NEW WORLD.
EACH OF YOU HAVE A MAP TO YOUR
CAMPS.
HEAD OUT AND GET STARTED.
GOOD LUCK.
>> NOW I HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO
SHOW ALL THOSE DUMP ASSES HOW
BIG A MISTAKE THEY MADE.
>> GIVE ME A HUG.
>> GREAT TO BE HERE.
WAY TO GO.
>> IT'S AN HONOR TO PLAY WITH
YOU GUYS.
>> LET'S DO WHATEVER WE CAN TO
DO.
LET'S NOT SHE JEFF AT IMMUNITY.
>> I'D MUCH RATHER SEE TYSON RUN
AROUND NAKED.
>> LET'S POP OFF OUR SHIRTS.
>> ALL RIGHTY, THEN.
>> DO IT!
>> IT'S BEEN 13 YEARS SINCE
PLAYED "SURVIVOR."
I THINK IN THE THE LONGEST
LAYOFF ANYBODY HAS HAD PLAYING
THE GAME.
IT'S GOING TO BE INTERESTING, TO
SAY THE LEAST.
I KNOW I'M UP FOR IT, THOUGH.
>> MACHETE.
>> I WAS EXCITED TO SEE WE HAD A
BOX THERE WITH SOME SUPPLIES IN
IT.
>> IS THERE ANY FLINT?
>> NO.
>> HEY, ON "HEROES-VILLAINS" I
WATCHED AND HELP ROB START FIRE
WITH BAMBOO.
WE CAN DO IT.
WE JUST NEED ENOUGH PEOPLE.
>> I THINK GALANG IS A STRONG
DESCRIBE IT'S BECAUSE WE HAVE A
LOT OF RETURNING PLAYERS, BUT
LAURA IS NOT GALANG.
SHE IS NOW, BUT SHE DIDN'T START
OFF THAT WAY.
I WANTED TO PLAY WITH RUPERT.
I DIDN'T WANT TO PLAY WITH
LAURA.
IF HER ASS GOT TO GO, GOOD-BYE.
PEACE!
SEE YOU LATER.
>> DAMN.
OKAY.
>> JOINING THE RETURNING
PLAYERS' TRIBE IS VERY
INTIMIDATING.
ALL THESE PEOPLE ARE THE
EXPERTS.
>> MOVE YOUR HAND OUT OF THE
WAY.
BUT TRY TO GET THE END OF IT.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU WANT ME TO HELP YOU?
>> IT'S HER FIRST TIME.
>> YOU NEED TO PRACTICE.
>> SO I'VE GOT A LOT OF PRESSURE
ON MY BACK.
I HAVE TO SHOW HOW TOUGH I AM
AND HOW VALUABLE I AM TO THE
TRIBE.
>> I SO WISH YOUR HUSBAND WAS
HERE RIGHT NOW, LAURA.
>> I KNOW I'M A LITTLE
DISAPPOINTING TO YOU GUYS.
>> NO, YOU'RE GREAT, YOU'RE
GREAT EYE DON'T MEAN TO BELITTLE
YOU.
I'M STOKED TO HAVE YOU.
>> YEAH, YEAH, THANK YOU.
I THINK THERE IS THE EXPECTATION
THEY AM LIKE RUPERT, BUT I'M NO
NOT.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY START THE
SHELTER.
>> LET'S GO.
>> WHOA!
>> THREE, TWO, ONE!
>> WHOOO!
>> YAY!
>> GO GET SOME STICKS.
>> BEING AN EXPERIENCED PLAYER
WE KNOW HOW IMPORTANT IT IS TO
HAVE FIRE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT YOUR SHELTER.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING ELSE
BECAUSE UNLESS YOU HAVE FIRE, WE
ARE DEAD IN THE WATER.
WITHIN 15 MINUTES, TYSON WENT
OUT THERE AND STARTED A FIRE.
>> ONCE WE GET THE FIRE HOT
ENOUGH, ANYTHING WILL BURN THAT
WE PUT IN IT.
>> IT'S BEEN NONSTOP.
WE'RE BOILING OUR WATER.
OUR CANTEENS ARE FULL.
>> WE'VE GOT WATER, GUYS.
>> WE'RE EATING OUR RICE.
MORAL IS GOOD.
IT'S AMAZING.
WE'RE REALLY COMFORTABLE AT THIS
POINT.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THIS IS, WHAT
I AM SUPPOSED TO DO, BUT... MY
NANNY NEVER LET ME PLAY WITH
SHARP TOOLS.
TOOLS.
>> GETTING TO PLAY "SURVIVOR"
NOT ONCE BUT TWICE AND BOTH
TIMES COLTON IS OUT HERE.
HE WAS SEEN AS ONE OF THE MOST
VINDICTIVE, VILLAINOUS, MEAN
PEOPLE TO EVER PLAY-OFF THE
GAME.
WE'RE ON THE SAME TRIBE.
WE DON'T NEED ANY DRAMA.
WE DON'T NEED ANYTHING TO HAPPEN
HERE, AND YOU HURT ME TO DEATH
LAST TIME.
A LOT AND I HOPE THAT WE CAN
BURY THAT AND NOT BE A NUISANCE
HERE AND MOVE ON.
I PLAYED WITH HIM BEFORE.
HE STABBED ME IN THE BACK.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE IT
HAPPEN
TO ME WHAT HAPPENED TO ME
BEFORE.
I CAN TRUST YOU?
OR ARE YOU GOING TO STAB ME IN
THE BACK AGAIN?
>> I THINK WE NEED TO TALK MORE
LATER, BUT, YES.
>> BUCK KNUCKLES.
>> HAS HE CHANGED?
HAS HE NOT?
I DON'T KNOW DOES A ZEBRA CHANGE
HIS STRIPES.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE, TOO.
WE'LL GET PASSED IT.
AM I ONCE AGAIN GOING TO BE
BAMBOOZLED?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I HAVE RELIVED MONICA'S
"SURVIVOR: ONE WORLD"
EXPERIENCE WITH HER, AND THEN
YOU'RE DROPPED OFF ON A BEACH
AND, WHOA, THERE'S NOTHING HERE.
WE'RE ON.
THERE WERE SOME BUTTERFLIES.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
THIS IS HOW IT'S GOING TO START.
>> I HAVEN'T SAWED SOMETHING
SINCE I WAS LIKE A KID.
BEING A YOGA TEACHER, THESE
HANDS DON'T SEE A HARD DAY'S
WORK.
>> SO WE'RE ALL WORKING HARD
AROUND CAMP.
THE BOYS ARE MAKING THE SHELTER.
THE GIRLS ARE WEAVING THE PALM
FRONDS.
WE HAVE NO VETERANS HERE SO
WE'RE ALL GOING ON WHAT OUR
LOVED ONES TOLD US AND BASICALLY
IT'S A BIT SHOCKING.
WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
>> THAT'S OKAY, THOUGH.
>> I FEEL LIKE I COULD BE IN
TROUBLE.
FIVE MINUTES INTO THE GAME I
MADE A HUGE BLUNDER ABOUT NOT
GOING 100% TO POTENTIALLY HELP
MY WIFE BECAUSE NOW SHE'S THE
ENEMY I NEED TO PUT SOMETHING TO
REST REALLY QUICK.
IN THE FIRST MOMENTS OF THE
GAME, I MENTIONED SOMETHING
ABOUT-- HERE'S THE DEAL.
I PROMISE YOU, IN A CHALLENGE,
YOU DON'T SEE ME GOING 100 PYOU
GOT MY BLESSING TO VOTE ME OUT.
I PROMISE YOU.
I'M GOING 100% FOR TADHANA OVER
GALANG.
>> AND WE'RE GOING TO RIDE YOU
BACK TO THE FINISH.
>> HE SAID HE'S NOT GOING TO
THROW A CHALLENGE FOR HIS WIFE.
BUT IT WASN'T AN APOLOGY?
EXACTLY.
I FEEL LIKE HE'S ONE I'M GOING
TO DEFINITELY HAVE TO KEEP MY
EYE ON AND KEEP HIM CLOSE
BECAUSE HE SEEMS LIKE HE COULD
BE A LOOSE CANNON.
>> WHERE ARE THE GUYS?
>> THIS IS NICE, BUDDY.
>> OH, MAN.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR."
>> THIS IS AWESOME.
>> MAN.
IF THERE'S ONE THING LEARNED
FROM MONICA.
SHE SAID, "BRAD, LOOK, WHEN YOU
PLAY THIS GAME, YOU BETTER HIT
THE GROUND RUNNING."
>> THIS IS KIND OF A NICE FIND.
>> YOU HIT THE GROUND RUNNING
TALKING TO PEOPLE.
YOU NEED TO MAKE CONNECTIONS.
YOU NEED GET AN ALLIANCE FAST.
>> WELL, THE KEY IS WE'VE GOT
FIVE GUYS RIGHT NOW.
WE'VE GOT FOUR GUYS AND A GAY
GUY.
WE'RE STRONG.
I'M TELLING YOU--
>> I THINK WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> YEENG WELGO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
VERY FAST, ANYWAY.
>> THE IDEA TO KEEP ALL THE FIVE
GUYS TOGETHER STEMMED FROM BRAD.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO LOVE
THE WATERFALL.
>> REALLY?
>> IT'S NOT A SURPRISE AT ALL.
SHOCKER.
THE GUY WHO PLAYED NFL FOOTBALL
WANTS TO KEEP HIS LOCKER ROOM
TOGETHER.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE MORE HE TALKS
ABOUT THAT KIND OF STUFF AND
ASSERTS HIMSELF A LEADER THE
MORE THAT COULD POTENTIALLY END
UP BITING HIM IN THE ASS LATER.
>> I'M THINKING WE GOT THE
NUMBERS WITH FIVE GUYS.
FIVE GUYS TOGETHER, THAT'S--
GOLD.
>> HOME RUN.
HERE'S THE DEAL.
THERE'S A FIVE-MAN ALLIANCE.
>> I THINK IT'S GENIUS.
>> I'M WILLING TO MAKE YOU
NUMBER ONE.
>> WHEN BRAD GOT ME BY MYSELF HE
WAS PRETTY MUCH TRYING TO
BULDY-BUDDY THE BROINANCE-TYPE
THING, ALL GUYS TO THE END, AND
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
LET'S SOUTHERN SHAKE ON IT.
A SOUTHERN MAN IS ONLY AS GOOD
AS HIS WORD.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
AND I'M THINKING YOU'RE WANTING
TO GET YOURSELF AND THEN YOUR
WIFE TO THE END AND WHOEVER
SHE'S WITH.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT STUPID.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER.
I'LL AGREE TO ANYTHING WITH HIM
AT THIS POINT BECAUSE IT WILL
SHUT HIM UP.
>> IF WE DO THE ALL FIVE GUY
THING WE CAN DWINLD THE GIRLS.
>> IT'S SO MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL
TO KEEP THE STRONG AROUND.
>> THESE DAYS, THE JOHN COCHRANS
OF "SURVIVOR" ARE THE BIG
THREATS NOW.
THOSE ARE THE PEOPLE WHO WIN.
THE WEAKER WOMEN, JOHN COCHRAN.
I THINK JOHN IS ON BOARD WITH
ALL FIVE.
EVERYBODY IS.
>> I GOT CALEB.
I GOT JOHN.
I GOT HAIND.
FIVE.
FOUR WITH NINE EQUALS OUT.
BUT I'M SORRY-- YEAH, NO.
-- OKAY.
FOUR WITH NINE EQUALS OUT.
BUT FIVE WITH NINE EQUALS IN.
>> IT'S ALMOST LIKE TOO EASY.
>> TOO EASY.
>> THE SHELTER'S COMING TOGETHER
MAN.
>> LET'S GET THIS OVER TO THE
OTHER SIDE.
>> WE CAN SLIDE THIS ON THE
BOTTOM.
>> THERE'S NO FLINT, AND NONE OF
US KNOW HOW TO START A FIRE
WITHOUT FLINT.
AND WE CAN'T BOIL OUR WATER.
JUST BUILDING THE SHELTER,
PUTTING IT TOGETHER, I CAN FEEL
THE LIQUID LEAVING MY BODY AND
I'M TURNING INTO SLUDGE.
>> HOW LONG YOU AND YOUR MAN
BEEN TOGETHER.
>> WE'VE BEEN MARRIED THREE
YEARS, BEEN TOGETHER THREE AND A
HALF, FOUR.
GOT MARRIED PRETTY QUICK.
>> SURE DID.
>> IS HE YUCK, TOO.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S THE BABY DADDY OF BOTH
OF THEM?
>> JUST MY SECOND ONE.
WHEN I GOT PREGNANT IN HOLLY, 16
AND PREGNANT TYPE STORY.
>> GOOD THING YOU DIDN'T GET
MARRIED.
>> DUDE, TELL ME ABOUT IT.
I ACTUALLY WAS A TEEN MOM SO I
GOT PREGNANT WHEN I WAS 17 IN
HOLLY.
THAT WAS A HUGE GAME CHANGER FOR
ME, AND MY MOM, IT WAS A REALLY
HARD OBSTACLE FOR US TO GET
THROUGH.
EXWARGS FOR MY MOM, PROBABLY.
>> AS A PARENT, THAT WOULD BE SO
HARD BECAUSE YOUR KIDS ARE
EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW?
I'M SURE IT WAS DIFFICULT FOR
YOUR MOM.
BUT IF MY DAUGHTER CAME HOME AND
SHE WAS 16 AND PREGNANT, I'D
EMBRACE HER AND SAY, "BABE, IT'S
OKAY.
LET'S DEAL WITH IT."
>> I DIDN'T TELL MY MOM.
>> REALLY.
>> THEY FOUND OUT EVENTUALLY.
WHEN YOUR PARENTS ARE CRYING,
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE THE WORST
PERSON EVER.
NOW IT'S GREAT.
AND MY HUSBAND IS GREAT.
>> YOUR MOM PROBABLY THINKS
BEING A GRANDPARENT OF TWO IS
BETTER THAN A GRANDPARENT OF
ONE.
>> I WAS IN JAIL WITH A GUY WHO
WAS ONE OF THE TOP-10 DEADBEAT
DAD.
>> YOU WERE IN JAIL.
>> I WAS A JUNKY, MAN.
I WAS A HEROINE ADDICT WHEN I
WAS A TEENAGER.
MY BROTHER WAS THE GOLDEN CHILD,
AND GOT A SCHOLARSHIP TO COLLEGE
PLAYING BASKETBALL, STRAIGHT-A
STUDENT EXPIRVETION JUST LIKE--
YOU KNOW.
>> OPPOSITE?
>> OMS.
DROPS OUT OF COLLEGE.
LIVING ON THE STREET, ROBBING
PEOPLE EVERY DAY TO GET MY FIX.
MY ADDICTION IMPACTED MY FAMILY
PROFOUNDLY.
EVEN MY RELATIONSHIP WITH MY
BROTHER TO THIS DAY IS STILL,
LIKE, NOT FULLY MENDED.
SO THIS IS A GREAT EXPERIENCE
I'M GOING TO GET TO HAVE WITH MY
BROTHER.
THE FACT THAT WE'RE GOING ON
THIS TOGETHER IS A PRETTY GREAT
OPPORTUNITY FOR US TO MEND SOME
MORE.
FINALLY GOT ARRESTED MAN PROBING
SOME LADY.
>> BEST THING THAT EVER HAPPENED
TO YOU?
>> BEST THING THAT HAPPENED TO
ME.
SAVED MY LIFE.
I OVERDOSED A FEW TIMES IN THE
PAST MONTH.
THE COPS FOUND ME ONE NIGHT IN
THE BATHROOM OF A GAS STATION
WITH A NEED IN MY ARM IT WAS TOO
POWERFUL.
>> AND YOU WERE JUST A BABY.
>> YEAH, A CHILD.
I THINK IN A GAME WHERE TRUST IS
THE MOST IMPORTANT PART.
I WANTED TO SHARE WITH MY TRIBE
MY PAST BECAUSE IF YOU WANT
SOMEBODY TO TRUST YOU, YOU HAVE
TO LET THEM IN LAILT BIT.
I WANT TO BE VULNERABLE AND SHOW
THEM.
THAT PART OF MY PAST MAKES ME
STRONGER.
>> OH, IT'S SO FRUSTRATING.
THAT WAS A GREAT JOB, THOUGH,
MAN.
>> MAYBE LIGHTNING WILL STRIKE
SOMETHING.
>> FOR ME, I DON'T THINK PEOPLE
THAT HEAR ABOUT THAT PART MIGHT
HAVE PAST ARE GOING TO THINK
ANYTHING LESS OF ME.
I DON'T THINK PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO SEE AN EX-CON THAT'S
CONNIVING AND A DOPE FIEND THAT
WILL DO WHATEVER HE CAN TO GET
WHAT HE WANTS.
I'VE GOT 14 YEARS CLEAN AND I
HAVE A LOT OF EXPERIENCE AWAY
FROM THAT.
AND I DO WANT TO SHOW THEM THAT
THERE'S A DIFFERENT PART OF ME
THAN JUST BEING A YOGA TEACHER.
AND I THINK IT WILL HELP
STRENGTHEN THE BONDS AND
CONNECTIONS I HAVE WITH THEM AND
WE'LL BE ABLE TO GET FURTHER IN
THIS GAME.
>> THIS TRIBE IS SO FUN.
FOR ME, PERSONALLY, EVERYONE
HERE KEEPS MY MIND OFF OF, LIKE
OTHER THE GAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S ALMOST LIKE I FORGET I'M IN
A GAME.
I THINK I JUST SIGNED UP FOR
SOME HORRIBLE CAMPING TRIP.
LAST TIME WHEN I PLAYED THIS
GAME HIGHER THIS MASK ON.
I WAS RUDE TO EVERYONE.
I WAS MEAN TO EVERYONE.
AND I DIDN'T HAVE KIND THINGS TO
SAY.
AND IT WAS ALL BECAUSE I WAS
INSECURE.
I ACTUALLY AM TRYING TO FIND AN
OPPORTUNITY TO REALLY TRY TO
EXPLAIN TO PEOPLE AND GET THEM
TO UNDERSTAND ME.
WHERE I'M FROM, I LIVE WITH NINE
MILLION PEOPLE IN MY STATE THAT
HAVE THE SAME BELIEFS.
WHAT I DON'T HAVE ARE PEOPLE
THAT ARE WILLING TO LISTEN.
I LIVE IN THE DEEP SOUTH WHERE
BEING GAY, IT'S A CROSS TO BEAR
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
WHEN I WAS GROWING UP, I WAS THE
SWEETEST KID IN THE WORLD.
AND, YOU KNOW, I MEAN, SOMEWHERE
ALONG THE WAY, I GOT TIRED OF
BEING CALLED SISSY AND FAGGOT,
AND YEAR.
QUEER.
THE STRUGGLE WAS GETTING PEOPLE
TOND I'M A LIVING HUMAN BEING
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
I HAVE BATTLE THE WITH MY OWN
FAMILY TRYING TO GET THEM TO
UNDERSTAND, AND THERE ARE PEOPLE
IN MY FAMILY THAT I DON'T HAVE
RELATIONSHIPS WITH BECAUSE THEY
DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT IT'S LIKE
OKAY TO LOVE ME.
AND SO...
>> OOOOH!
>> THE NEGATIVE EXPERIENCES THAT
YOU GO THROUGH IN LIFE, I THINK
THEY BUILD YOU TO THE PERSON
THAT YOU ARE, YOU KNOW, TODAY.
BUT I'M TRYING TO CHANGE.
I'M JUST GOING IN WITH POSITIVE
THINKING.
>> YOU'RE DOING AWESOME AND YOUR
GUY'S HERE UNDER THE SAME STARS
YOU ARE.
>> I JUST WANT TO SEE HIM.
>> I KNOW.
HE'S JUST AROUND THE CORNER.
YOU'LL SEE HIM TOMORROW.
FOR ALL OF US TO JUDGE WHAT
DECISIONS HE MAKES IS HARD.
WE HAVEN'T WALKED A MILE IN HIS
SHOES, AND I DON'T THINK IT'S
EASY.
IF HE'S CHANGED, WOULDN'T THAT
BE A BEAUTIFUL STORY?
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
>> BUT THEN AGAIN, IT'S COLTON.
>> KAT.
MONICA.
LAURA
THIS ONE IS FOR COLTON, JUST
LIKE THIS.
ONE OR TWO FOR EVERY PERSON WHO
VOTED FOR ME.
I DEFINITELY GOT MY FEEL, HURT
BY THE RETURNING PLAYERS' TRIBE,
AND I'M OUT FOR REVENGE.
I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO FIGHT AND TO WIN THIS GAME.
>> YOU WANT ME TO RIP IT APART?
>> NO, I GOT IT.
I GOT TO CHOP A COUPLE MORE
NAMES UP.
I'M REALLY JUST TRYING TO KEEP
MY MIND IN THE GAME AND MAINTAIN
THE CAMP SO THAT I CAN STAY
HEALTHY, HYDRATED, AND READY TO
BEAT RUPERT.
>> NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS
WOULD I HAVE GUESSED I WOULD BE
IN THIS POSITION ON THE SECOND
DAY.
>> ME, NEITHER.
LIVING WITH RUPERT IS EXTREMELY
ANNOYING, TO SAY THE LEAST.
>> I'M GOING BACK IN THE WATER.
>> OKAY.
RUPERT MOSTLY IS EITHER SLEEPING
OR SPLASHING AROUND IN THE
WATER.
I GET THE COCONUT.
I GET ALL THE FIREWOOD.
I GO GET ALL THE WATER.
I TEND THE FIRE.
I BOIL THE WATER.
I BOIL THE RICE.
AND RUPERT ENJOYS THE SPOILS.
IT'S INFURIATING, ACTUALLY.
>> SEE HOW COMFORTABLE A BED WE
GOT.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THE FLAT
BOARDS ARE EVEN MORE COMFORTABLE
THAN THE DAMN BAMBOO.
I AM NOT GOING TO DO WHAT I'VE
DONE SO MANY OTHER TIMES.
ONE OF THE REASONS WHY I'VE
NEVER WON AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
IS I KILL MYSELF OUT FISHING.
I KILL MYSELF OUT TAKING CARE OF
MY TRIBE.
( SNORING )
BUT THIS IS MORE INDIVIDUAL.
AND IF I'M GOING TO BEAT
CANDICE, I NEED EVERY OUNCE OF
ENERGY I GOT.
IF CANDICE WANTS TO GO OUT AND
KILL HERSELF GATHERING WOOD AND
MAKING FIRE AND KEEPING IT GOING
AND BOILING WATER AND DOING
EVERYTHING, GREAT!
BURN UP HER ENERGY.
I'M NOT GOING TO.
AND I NEED TO HAVE IN MY HEAD
THAT I WILL ELIMINATE HER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THERE IT IS.
>> TREE MAIL.
>> RACHEL AND I GET UP AND WENT
TO CHECK TREE MAIL.
WE'RE LIKE OFFICIAL "SURVIVOR"
PEOPLE NOW ALL RIGHT.
>> IT LOOKS PRETTY.
>> YEAH.
IT'S REALLY EXCITING.
UNTIL YOU'VE GOTTEN SOMETHING IN
TREE MAIL YOU HAVEN'T STARTED
THE GAME.
>> I'LL CARRY THE FLAG.
YOU CARRY THE MAIL.
>> I FEEL LIKE SANTA CLAUS.
>> WHOOO!
>> TREE MAIL, TREE MAIL.
>> I FEEL GREAT GOING INTO THE
CHALLENGE.
THE ADVANTAGE THAT WE HAVE AS
RETURNING PLAYERS IS WE KNOW
KEEP YOUR HEAD IN IT, KEEP CALM.
BECAUSE ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
>> EQUAL OF "WILL YOU CHOOSE TO
STEP FORWARD TO RUN, JUMP, AND
SWIM?
WILL YOU PADDLE STRAIGHT THE
FIRST TIME, YOUR CHANCES ARE
PRETTY SLIM."
>> "OR SHOULD YOU ASSEMBLE THE
PIECES TO MAKE THE FLAG REALLY
SPIN?
WILL YOU BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
WELL, NOT IF YOU WIN."
>> THIS IS AWESOME.
I THINK THIS IS MADE FOR US.
>> RIGHT AWAY WE'RE TRYING TO
THINK WHO IS THE FASTEST
SWIMMER, WHO IS GOOD AT
SPLINTING.
WHO IS GOOD AT PUZZLES.
>> I ALREADY KNOW MY MOTHER IS
GOING TO DO THE PUZZLE.
>> ARE YOU BETTER THAN HER.
>> YES.
>> MY MOM IS GREAT AT PUZZLES,
TOO.
SHE'S PROBABLY ON THE PUZZLE.
I'M ON THE PUZZLE.
IT'S GOING TO BE THE
MOTHER-DAUGHTER DUEL.
>> YOU TWO ON THE PUZZLE AGAINST
YOUR MOM, AND THEN BEAT YOUR
ASS.
THAT WOULD BE SO AWESOME.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU'RE
NOT A FAST SWIMMER, JIMMER.
IT'S ABOUT THE PUZZLE.
>> PUZZLES ARE MY STRENGTH.
THINK OUTSIDE THE BOX.
HOW DO WE DO DO THIS QUICKER.
>> MOMS ALWAYS SAY, "I BROUGHT
YOU INTO THIS WORLD.
I CAN TAKE YOU OUT."
>> AS MUCH AS I LOVE HER,
UNFORTUNATELY, I WANT TO BEAT MY
DAUGHTER IN THIS GAME.
SORRY, CIERA.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS, LAURA,
MOMENTS INTO THE GAME-- YOU
ALREADY KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO
ASK YOU.
YOU WANT YOUR REAL COLORS.
>> I WANT MY COLORS.
I'M A MEMBER OF THIS TEAM.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE OFFICIALLY A
MEMBER OF GALANG.
HERE YOU GO.
YOU CAN DROP YOUR RED ONE, LEAVE
IT THERE.
NO SOUVENIRS IN THIS GAME.
COLTON, HOW HAS IT BEEN THE
FIRST FEW DAYS OUT HERE?
HAVE YOU GUYS HAD ANY LUCK WITH
CAMP, FIRE, ANY OF THE
NECESSITIES?
>> YEAH, WE HAVE FIRE.
WE HAVE SHELTER.
>> Jeff: HOW DID YOU GET FIRE?
>> TEAM EFFORT.
>> TYSON.
>> 15 MINUTES IN, HE HAD OUR
FIRE GOING.
GOT WATER BOILING.
WE ARE HYDRATED.
>> WE'RE READY.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: BRAD, DO YOU BELIEVE
THEY HAVE FIRE?
IS IT POSSIBLE THEY'RE JUST
SAYING THAT?
>> POSSIBLY.
BUT THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOOD.
>> DO YOU GUYS NOT HAVE FIRE?
>> WE'VE GOT FIRE.
>> WE GOT PLENTY IT.
WE CAN SHARE IT WITH YOU IF YOU
WANT.
>> WE DON'T NEED TO.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS HAVE FIRE AS
WELL?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT TOOK US A WHILE.
>> THEY PROBABLY HAVE FIRE
BECAUSE THEY HAVE EXPERIENCE.
WE DON'T, BECAUSE WE'RE A BUNCH
OF MEATHEADS.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING
TO WORK ON MY GO, SIX MEMBERS OF
EACH TRIBE WILL RACE OVER A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES TO A BOAT.
YOU'LL INTIE IT AND PADDLE IT
BACK.
ON THAT BOAT, YOU'LL FIND A
CHEST AND FULL OF PUZZLE PIECES.
THE THREE REMAINING TRIBE
MEMBERS WILL USE THOSE PUZZLE
PIECES TO ASSEMBLE A SHIP'S
WHEEL.
FIRST TRIBE TO ASSEMBLE THEIR
WHEEL AND USE IT TO RAISE THEIR
FLAG WINS IMMUNITY.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT IN THIS
GAME.
IMMUNITY KEEPS YOU SAFE FROM
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
TRIBAL COUNCIL IS NOT WHERE YOU
WANT TO BE.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
IT IS OUR FIRST CHALLENGE IN
"BLOOD VERSUS WATER."
ONLY WAY YOU ENSURE YOU DON'T GO
TO TRIBAL IS BY BEATING THE
OTHER TRIBE WHICH IS FULL OF
YOUR LOVED ONES.
COMPLICATES THE GAME.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND FIRE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GOTTA GET UP AND OVER THAT NET.
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO GET OVER IT.
>> COME ON, TYSON!
>> WHOOO!
GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES OFF TO A
PRETTY GOOD START A LOT OF TEAM
WORK WITH THE NEW PLAYERS
TADHANA, TADHANA WORKING
TOGETHER WELL.
>> LET'S GO, GERVASE.
>> GO, COLTON!
>> Jeff: NEW PLAYERS OFF TO AN
EARLY LEAD.
TADHANA CONTINUED TO WORK
TOGETHER VERY WELL.
JOHN PULLING RACHEL.
PULLS MARISSA OVER.
>> COME ON, ARAS!
>> Jeff: THE RETURNING PLAYERS
ARE STRUGGLING.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: COLTON TRYING TO GET
OVER.
GERVASE IS OVER.
ARAS IS ON HIS OWN.
NOBODY IS HELPING ARAS.
YOU CAN'T MOVE FORWARD UNTIL
YOU'RE ON THE PLATFORM.
ARAS IS OVER.
GO, TADHANA.
THE NEW PLAYERS WITH THE LEAD.
EARLY IN THIS FIRST CHALLENGE.
RETURNING PLAYERS ARE STILL
STRUGGLING.
GERVASE COULD BARELY GET UP ON
THE PLATFORM.
HE'S EXHAUSTED.
BIG LEAD FOR THE NEW PLAYERS.
GERVASE STILL TRYING TO GET HIS
WIND BACK.
CAN BARELY GET UP THESE CRAITS.
REALLY SLOWING HIS TRIBE DOWN.
>> COME ON, TADHANA!
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT TO UNTIE A
SERIES OF KNOTS TO RELEASE THAT
BOAT.
GERVASE CAN BARELY GET UP.
AND THEN A HORRIBLE BELLY FLOP.
>> COME ON!
COME ON, GERVASE.
>> ARAS HELP ME.
>> Jeff: GERVASE IS STRUGGLING
TO SWIM.
ARAS DOING WHAT HE CAN THOP HIM.
BOTH TRIBES NOW WORKING ON THEIR
KNOTS.
>> LET'S GO, AQUA MAN.
>> Jeff: ARAS STILL HELPING
GERVASE.
STILL NOT TO THE BOAT.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THE KNOTS
UNTIED, AND EVERYBODY IS ON THE
BOAT, YOU CAN START PADDLING.
ARAS FINALLY GETS GERVASE BACK
TO THE BOAT WHILE THE REST OF
THE TRIBE HAS BEEN UNTYING THE
KNOTS.
THE NEW PLAYERS HAVE THEIR BOAT
UNTIED.
THE RETURNING PLAYERS HAVE THEIR
BOAT UNTIED.
THEY'RE READY TO GO.
START PADDLING, GALANG.
>> YAY!
>> PULL!
PULL!
3.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT TO GO DOWN
THE MIDDLE.
THE RETURNING PLAYERS JUST
RECOVERED FROM GERVASE' SWIMMING
AND NOW THEY DON'T KNOW HOW TO
PADDLE.
>> COME ON!
>> PADDLE, COLTON.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN THE NEW
PLAYERS, TADHANA, ARE IN THE
LEAD.
>> LET'S GO!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: THE RETURNING PLAYERS
ARE STRUGGLING AGAINST THE NEW
PLAYERS.
THIS IS WHERE YOU SEE WHAT A
TRIBE IS MADE OF!
>> GIVE ME THE PADDLE.
PADDLE STRONG, COLTON!
>> Jeff: ONCE YOU'RE CLIPPED
IN, BRING THAT CRATE UP.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
>> COME ON, COME ON, COME ON!
>> COME ON, GUYS!
COME ON!
>> Jeff: MORE DYSFUNCTION WITH
THE RETURNING PLAYERS.
ONCE THEY'RE THEY'RE SIDEWAYS.
>> PADDLE.
>> PADDLE!
>> OH, HELL NO.
OH, I WILL.
>> Jeff: HUGE ADVANTAGE FOR
TADHANA.
PATHETIC BEGINNING FOR THE
PLAYERS WHO KNOW HOW TO PLAY
THIS GAME, GETTING SHOWN UP BY
THEIR LOVED ONES.
>> COME ON, COME ON!
>> LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: TIMELY.
GALANG IS BACK.
THE RETURNING PLAYERS HAVE A LOT
OF TIME TO MAKE PUP.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: NEW PLAYERS HAVE HAD
A LOT OF TIME TO START WORKING
ON THIS PUZZLE.
>> COME OONE MORE.
>> Jeff: IT'S CALEB, CIERA,
AND KATIE WORKING ON THE PUZZLE
FOR THE NEW PLAYERS.
IT IS LAURA, MONICA, AND TINA
WORKING ON THE PUZZLE FOR THE
RETURNING PLAYERS.
>> THAT'S IT, THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: OUR FIRST CHALLENGE,
AND THE NEWBIES ARE INTENT
INTOANT SHOWING THE RETURNING
PLAYERS, THEIR LOVED ONES, THAT
THIS IS GOING TO BE A BATTLE.
>> COME ON, GIRLS.
>> Jeff: THIS IS WHERE
EXPERIENCE COMES INTO PLAY.
NOT PANICKING.
>> I DON'T KNOW, GUYS.
>> LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
>> Jeff: CIERA AND CALEB
WORKING FAST.
KATIE TRYING TO FIND HER PLACE.
THE WOMEN OF GALANG WORKING
TOGETHER WELL, MAKING UP A LOT
OF TIME KATIE STRUGGLING EVEN TO
GET HER PIECES TO FIT.
ALL THE ADVANTAGE THAT THE SIX
PEOPLE IN THE WATER GAVE THEM IS
GONE.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: RETURNING PLAYERS
VERY CLOSE.
>> YOU GOT IT, GIRLS.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> HOLD IT UP, HOLD IT UP!
>> Jeff: AFTER SUFFERING A
HUGE SETBACK, THE RETURNING
PLAYERS ARE NOW BACK IN THE
LEAD.
>> FASTER, COME ON!
>> LET'S GO, WE GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: SUDDENLY THE NEWBIES
ARE IN TROUBLE.
>> LET'S GO.
>> WHOO!
>> Jeff: RETURNING PLAYERS
WORKING ON THAT SECOND BAG.
THE NEW PLAYERS STILL
STRUGGLING.
THREE OF THE OLDER WOMEN IN THIS
GAME USING THEIR EXPERIENCE TO
PUT THEIR TRIBE BACK AHEAD
RETURNING PLAYERS ARE NOW ON THE
THIRD BAG OF PUZZLE PIECES.
>> YOU GOT TBABY.
>> Jeff: THE NEWBIES STILL
STRUGGLING TO FINISH THEIR FIRST
BACK.
WOW, AMAZING.
ABSOLUTE COLLAPSE AT THE PUZZLE
STAGE FOR THE NEW TRIBE TADHANA.
>> COME OGIRLS.
>> Jeff: TWO MOTHERS SCHOOLING
THEIR DAUGHTERS RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS THE FINAL PHASE OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
AND THEY ARE FLYING.
THE RETURNING PLAYERS ARE ABOUT
TO DELIVER A LESSON TO THEIR
LOVED ONES.
AND IT SOUNDS LIKE THIS.
GALANG WINS IMMUNITY!
AND FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
>> DON'T LET THEM FOOL YOU,
BABY!
DON'T LET THAT FOOL YOU!
>> SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
>> DON'T LET THAT FOOL YOU!
>> Jeff: RETURNING PLAYERS,
GALANG, SHOWING YOUR LOVED ONES
HOWING IT DONE.
IMMUNITY AND FIRE IN THE FORM OF
FLINT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: COLTON, YOU'RE
CRYING.
COLTON, ARE YOU UPSET BECAUSE
YOU THINK HE'S IN TROUBLE OR
JUST... THE FACT THAT YOU KNOW
YOU JUST SENT HIM TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> PROBABLY BOTH, JEFF.
I THINK HE'S PROBABLY FEELING
WHAT ALL OF US DO IS IT'S A
BITTERSWEET.
WE WON, BUT WE PUT OUR LOVED
ONES IN JEOPARDY.
>> SHHH.
IT'S OKAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GALANG.
ENJOY YOUR NIGHT OFF FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
CONGRATS.
>> THANK YOU.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: TADHANA, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND WHERE THEY
WILL HAVE TO COMPETE IN DUELS IN
ORDER TO STAY ALIVE.
WHICH MEANS TONIGHT AS A GROUP
YOU WILL VOTE SOMEBODY OUT WHO
WILL THEN VOTE AND COMPETE,
JOHN, AGAINST YOUR WIFE.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> MEAN, FOR GERVASE TO JUMP UP
AND DOWN IN YOUR FACE.
I WAS LIKE, HEY, BOWES OH, YOUR
LOVED ONE MAY GO HOME.
WHILE YOU'RE CHEERING ABOUT
THAT, THAT'S GREAT, YOU BEAT US.
BUT IT'S LIKE YOU'RE BEATING
YOUR OWN.
>> GUYS, YOU PLAYED HARD.
EVERYBODY DID.
LY WORK FORCE THE CHALLENGE AND
THAT STINKS.
I DIDN'T GET TO WHERE I AM IN
LIFE BY LOSING AND I HATE TO
LOVE.
>> OUR LOVED ONES HAVE FIRE.
LET'S BE HAPPY.
THERE'S A SILVER LINING.
LET'S BE HAPPY THEY HAVE FIRE.
>> WE'RE NOT DYING WITHOUT IT.
>> I KNOW THIS EYE DON'T THINK
THERE'S A SINGLE PERSON WHO
DIDN'T GIVE 100%.
LISTEN, PUZZLE MAKERS, OF IT A
TOUGH PUZZLE.
YOU'RE BEATING YOURSELF UP,
DON'T.
>> THEY'VE ALL DONE THIS.
THEY KNOW THE EXPERIENCE.
THEY WEREN'T AS NERVOUS.
THIS IS THE NOT THE FIRST TIME
THOSE THREE LADIES HAVE DONE A
PUZZLE.
>> YOU CAN'T DISCOUNT
EXPERIENCE.
>> AFTER OUR FIRST CHALLENGE MY
HEART SANK TO THE FLOOR.
IT WAS THE FIRST CHALLENGE AND
THE FIRST LOSS AND I KNEWIS PART
OF WHY THE TEAM LOST.
I GOT CREAMED BY MY MOTHER, AND
THE FACT THAT THE THREE OF US,
WANT PUZZLE PEOPLE, WERE THE
REASON THAT WE DIDN'T PULL
THROUGH AT THE END,UN, THAT
MAKES ME A LITTLE NERVOUS.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO JUDGE THE
VOTES OFF OF.
>> POOR GERVASE, MAN.
>> NOT POOR GERVASE.
HE WAS THE LOUDEST ONE, LIKE,
"THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT!"
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> HE IS SO FREAKING
COMPETITIVE.
I WAS NOT EXPECTING HIM TO THROW
IT IN MY FACE LIKE THAT.
I WAS JUST LIKE, GERVASE.
CALM DOWN.
YOU JUST SHOWED YOU'RE THE
WEAKEST ATHLETIC PERSON ON YOUR
TRIBE WITH THAT SWIM,
PERFORMANCE.
I DO THINK THE OTHER TRIBE WAS
CELEBRATING TOO MUCH AFTER THAT
WIN BECAUSE THEY ARE OUR LOVED
ONES.
YES, YOU WON, BUT GUESS WHAT?
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEND ONE OF US
HOME.
WHO ARE THEY GOING TO CORRELATE
GERVASE WITH?
HIS NIECE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO WIN SOME
CHALLENGES, AND LET'S WIN WITH
GRACE.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS THEY WERULE
JUMPING AROUND--
>> WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS THE
LION DOES NOT ROAR AFTER IT
KILLS ITS PREY.
>> THEY WERE ROARING AFTER
KILLING THEIR CUBS.
AND THE CUBS LOOK AT THEM AND
GO, HMM.
DOESN'T MAKE ME HAPPY.
I DON'T WANT TO GLOAT OVER THEM
BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING TO LOSE A
LOVED ONE.
>> THE WAY IT WORKED OUT, GUYS
VERSUS THE GIRLS, 5-4.
THERE WERE SEASONS PEOPLE WOULD
KILL TO BE IN THE NUMBERS EARLY
ON.
>> WE HAVE FIVE STRONG.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BREAK IT UP.
NOBODY IS GOING TO DRIVE A NAIL
IN THIS.
>> THE SOONER WE CAN FIGURE THIS
OUT, THE LESS STRESS THERE WILL
BE.
WHOEVER WE VOTE OUT, WE HAVE TO
REMEMBER, IS GOING TO BE A STAB
IN SOMEBODY'S HEART TONIGHT.
>> YEAH.
YOU--
>> I WAS JACKED UP.
I-- I'M TELLING YOU, IT FELT
LIKE SUNDAY AGAIN.
IT IS.
OPENING KICKOFF.
>> AND I KNOW MONICA.
I SAW HER OVER THERE.
AND HER WHEELS-- I DON'T KNOW.
I'M GLAD SHE DIDN'T REALLY GLOAT
THAT MUCH.
>> I THINK THERE'S SUCH A THING
AS BEING A SORE WINNER, TOO.
>> AND THAT WAS ROUGH.
I DIDN'T LIKE THAT.
I NOTICED THAT.
I UNDERSTAND BEING HAPPY.
BUT THERE'S A POINT WHERE WE
NEED TO BE SMART ABOUT IT.
I'LL TELL YOU I'M A LITTLE
SPOILED ON MARISSA RIGHT NOW
JUST BECAUSE OF THE WAY GERVASE
ACTED.
MARIS ABEFORE WE WENT TO THE
CHALLENGE, HE WAS A LITTLE BIT
OFF THE RADAR, BUT THERE'S A
SIDE OF MYSELF THAT SAW GERVASE
JUMPING UP AND DOWN AND KIND OF
IN YOUR FACE "WE WON."
SHE'S GOING HOME.
HOW DO YOU LIKE THOSE APPLES.
GERVASE AIN'T THE PLAYER HE WAS
THEN.
I AM NOT BLAMING ANYBODY ON THE
PUZZLE THEMSELVES.
I'M THINKING GOING FORWARD WHO
WILL BE OUR BEST ASSET.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> KATIE WAS KIND OF LIKE A
THIRD WHEEL.
>> WE WERE CONCERNED ABOUT HER,
TOO.
WITH THE PUZZLE PART, IT WAS
CIERA, KATIE, AND ME.
AND CIERA REALLY JUMPED IN.
SHE WAS REALLY HELPFUL.
AND IT JUST SEEMED LIKE KATIE,
SHE WAS THE EXTRA COOK IN THE
KITCHEN.
>> HERE'S THE THING, KATIE IS A
SMART GIRL AND SHE GOT TO THE
PUZZLE AND--
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE KATIE GO,
BUT IF THE MAJORITY'S IN, THEN
I'M IN WITH IT.
>> BUT WE DO NEED TO THINK ABOUT
KEEPING THE TRIBE STRONG.
>> THE GIRLS PROBABLY KNOW THAT
THE GUY BONDED.
I MEAN, WE'RE NOT BEING SULT AT
ALL TO THESE WOMEN SO IT'S
IMPORTANT FOR ME TO KEEP MY
ALLIANCES WITH THE GIRLS STRONG.
I'M GOING TO TELL THE GIRLS,
HEY, GIETS HAVE DECIDE WHICH ONE
WILL GO FIRST.
SOME OF THE GUYS CAME AND WERE
TALKING ABOUT MARISSA BECAUSE
GERVASE AT THE END.
>> GOTCHA.
>> I THINK IN THE END THEY
DECIDE PEOPLE DECIDED THAT IT
WOULD BE THE PUZZLE BUILDERS.
KATIE.
>> LET'S BE HONEST.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHOEVER THEY
CHOOSE TO VOTE FOR.
THE GUYS HAVE DEFINITELY BONDED
WITH EACH OTHER.
I FEEL BAD FOR THE GIRLS.
BUT AT THIS POINT IT WOULD BE
FOOLISH TO TRY TO GO AGAINST
THAT.
>> WE'RE FIVE GUYS STRONG.
ONE OF THE GIRLS HAS TO GO.
SO IT MAY BE MARISSA.
IT MAY BE KATIE.
TO ME, THEY'RE ALL EQUAL OPINION
THE GIRLS ARE BOTH CONNECTED
WITH THE OTHER TRIBE.
WE'VE GOT TO START THINKING
ABOUT WHO WE VOTE OUT COULD
POTENTIALLY AFFECT THEIR TRIBE.
>> Jeff: GO AHEAD AND GRAB A
TORCH.
APPROACH THE FLAME, DIP IT IN,
AND GET FIRE
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IN THIS GAIRNLG FIRE REPRESENTS
YOUR LIFE
ALL RIGHT, FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
NOT THE PLACE YOU WANT TO BE,
BUT SOMEBODY'S GET TO BE HERE.
HAYDEN, WHAT'S BEEN THE TOUGHEST
PART OF THE FIRST FEW DAYS FOR
YOU?
>> TRYING TO CREATE FIRE.
>> Jeff: SO YOU GUYS WERE
LYING TO ME TODAY.
YOU DONT HAVE FIRE.
>> YEAH, WE WERE TOTAL BLUFFING.
>> Jeff: SKIER AYOU HAD TO
TALK TO YOUR MOM A LOT ABOUT HER
EXPERIENCE OUT HERE.
HOW MUCH MORE DIFFICULT IS IT
ONCE YOU'RE OUT HERE.
>> HAVING MY MOM TELL ME STORIES
AND ACTUALLY BEING OUT HERE IS
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
I MEAN, I'VE NEVER BEEN THIS
HUNGRY.
I'M LIKE, OKAY, SOMEBODY IS JUST
TRYING TO GET OUT OF MY RIGHT
NOW, CLAWING AT MY INSIDE, SO TO
EXPERIENCE IT IS REALLY ROUGH.
>> Jeff: CULL CULPEPPER,
YOU'RE THREE DAYS IN AND
OBVIOUSLY STRUGGLING.
>> IT'S FRUSTRATING NOT HAVING
FIRE.
IF WE GET FIRE WE COOK AND GET
STRONG AND WIN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGEES.
>> Jeff: CALEB, HOW DOES
HAVING LOVED ONES ON THE OTHER
TRIBE CHANGE THIS GAME?
>> IT DOES COMPLICATE IT.
HE DOESN'T WHAT'S GOING ON OVER
THERE JUST LIKE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON OVER THERE.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST EACH OTHER
THAT THEY'RE GOING TO DO THE
RIGHT THING.
RIGHT NOW, THEY'RE DOING THEIR
THING AND WE HAVE TO DO OUR
THING.
>> Jeff: MOMENTS INTO DAY ONE,
THE WOMAN YOU LOVE IS VOTED OUT.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: YOU WERE GIVEN THE
CHANCE TO TAKE HER SPOT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY REGRETS ABOUT
NOT TAKING HER SPOT?
>> I HAVE A LOT OF REGRETS.
AS A HUSBAND IT'S SOMETHING I
STRUGGLE WITH AND I FEEL LIKE...
I JUST EYE FEEL LIKE CANDICE IS
PROBABLY SITTING THERE ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND THINKING I
JUST... JUST... LET HER GO.
AND JUST, LIKE LET HER DOWN,
DIDN'T STAND UP FOR HER.
I'M HOPING SHE'S NOT THINKING
THAT BUT IT'S SOMETHING I'VE
BEEN STRUGGLING WITH A LITTLE
BIT.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THAT IMPACT--
YOU, KNOWING WHOEVER YOU VOTE
OUT TONIGHT LBL COMPETING
AGAINST YOUR WIFE AND RUPERT IN
THE FIRST DUEL AT REDEMPTION?
>> IF TODAY'S CHALLENGE SPEAKS
TO ANYTHING, IT REALLY SHOWS
THAT OUR LOVED ONES ON THE OTHER
TRIBE ARE NOT GOING TO PULL ANY
PUNCHES.
SO MY VOTE TONIGHT IS GOING TO
BE WAISED ON WHO I THINK IS
GOING TO MAKE THIS TRIBE
STRONGEST GOING FORWARD.
IF THERE IS AN ADDED ADVANTAGE
THEY I THINK CANDICE CAN KICK
WHOEVER'S BUTT, THAT'S GREAT,
TOO.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER, WHERE DO
YOU SEE THIS GAME GOING, THE
BLOOD VERSUS THE WATER?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
>> I THINK IT WAS AN INTERESTING
DYNAMIC TODAY WHEN WE LOST
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY'RE
CELEBRATING SO MUCH ON THEIR END
BECAUSE ONE OF THEIR LOVED ONES
IS GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: WHO WAS CELEBRATING?
WHO STOOD OUT?
>> Jeff: GERVASE.
>> Jeff: MARISSA, YOU'RE
SHAKING YOUR HEAD AT YOUR OWN
UNCLE.
>> YES, BECAUSE THEY WERE
CELEBRATING LIKE THAT.
I THINK OF THEM AS VETERANS,
MORE MATURE, WISER.
I WAS EXPECTING THEM TO HANDLE
IT WITH GRACE.
>> Jeff: VYTAS CIT WORK
AGAINST YOU IF YOUR LOVED ONE
BEHAVES THIS WAY?
>> OF COURSE, SOMEBODY GLOATING
IN OUR FACE ADDS INSULT TO
INJURY.
THIS TWIST IS DIFFERENT THAN ANY
OTHER SEASON.
NO TEAM WHO WINS IMMUNITY IS
WORRYING THE NIGHT THE THE OTHER
TEAM GOES TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I GUARANTEE YOU TONIGHT, THAT
TEAM IS WORRYING, BECAUSE WHEN
THEY SEE US THE NEXT TIME AT A
CHALLENGE.
THANE ONE OF THEIR LOVED ONES IS
GOING TO BE GONE.
>> Jeff: MARIS ACONCERNED AT
ALL WE WHAT VYTAS SAID?
>> YES, BECAUSE I'M GUILTY BY
ASSOCIATION.
I WISH GERVASE WOULD HAVE
PIEPPED DOWN AT THE MOMENT SO I
WOULD FEEL A LITTLE LESS
VULNERABLE RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: WOW.
THAT WOULD BE DEVASTATING TO GET
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME FOR
SOMETHING YOU DIDN'T DO BUT YOUR
UNCLE DID.
>> EXACTLY.
BUT, I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE SHOULD
JUST BE JUDGING ME ON MY
PERFORMANCE, MY CHARACTER, MY
ADD OF ATTITUDE, NOT MY LOVED
ONE'S.
IT COMES DOWN TO OUR TRIBE, NOT
WHAT THEIR TRIBE IS DOING.
WAIT UNTIL WE GET TO THE MERGE
AND THEN YOU CAN DECIDE IF YOU
WANT TO JUDGE ME BECAUSE OF HIS
ACTIONS.
>> Jeff: KATIE, WHERE WERE YOU
AT FOR THE FIRST VOTE?
YOU VALLEY SO LITTLE TO GO ON?
>> I MEAN, THE CHALLENGE TODAY,
I THINK THE FIRST LEG OF THE
RACE, THE GUYS DID REALLY GREAT.
AND THE PUZZLE MAKERS FELL
BEHIND AND SO THE FEAR TONIGHT
IS BASED OFF OF THE CHALLENGE.
THAT'S ONE THING TO JUDGE OUR
VOTES OFF OF.
SO, YOU KNOW, THERE IS SOME
FEAR.
>> Jeff: WOULD IT BE FAIR TO
VOTE YOU OFF FOR ONE POOR
PERFORMANCE IN YOUR FIRST-EVER
"SURVIVOR" CHALLENGE?
>> I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER, IF YOU
HAVE TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT, AND
YOU CAN'T FIND ANY OTHER REASON,
THEN IT COULD BE TODAY'S
CHALLENGE.
>> YEAH, OBVIOUSLY, IF THEY HAD
HAVE BEEN SUCCESSFUL IT WOULD
HAVE ELEVATED THEIR LEVEL IN THE
TRIBE RIGHT NOW.
BUT I DON'T THINK WE'RE ALL
JUDGING SOLELY ON THE
PERFORMANCE OF THE PUZZLE
MAKERS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
CALEB, YOU'RE UP.
>> MARACE, YOU'RE A GREAT GIRL,
BUT I'M SORRY, THE GAME HAS
STARTED.
>> IT'S EITHER YOU OR ME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KATIE.
MARISSA.
TWO VOTES MARISSA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES MARISSA, ONE
VOTE KATIE.
MARISSA.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES MARISSA.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. WATER,"
MARISSA.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
MARIS ATHE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL, FIRST
BLINDSIDE.
YOUR FAMILY MEMBERS HAVE TAUGHT
YOU HOW TO PLAY THIS GAME.
THE FACT THAT YOU'RE HERE SAYS
THEY DIDN'T TEACH YOU
EVERYTHING.
GOOD NEWS ABOUT COMING TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, YOU WILL NOW HAVE FIRE
>> I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions and CBS
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> I'M SO SICK OF THIS.
I CAN'T DEAL WITH THREE MORE
DAYS OF KUMBAYA.
>> Jeff: THE OLD COLTON IS
BACK.
>> HE'S A BULLY.
>> HOPEFULLY THIS CAMP WILL
ERUPT INTO CHAOS.
>> Jeff: TWO PEOPLE WILL STAY
ALIVE.
ONE IS GOING HOME FOR GOOD.
AND THE FIRST DUEL AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND TAKES ITS TOLL ON
EVERYONE.
>> HEY!
>> ANOTHER BLINDSIDE.
>> I JUST GOT BLINDSIDED AT
TRIBAL.
I CAME IN THINKING THAT KATIE'S
THE GO.
NO, MARISSA IS THE GO.
>> I'M JUST REALLY PISSED.
>> THIS IS REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WHERE A BUNCH OF PEOPLE SIT
PISSED OFF.