>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AT GALANG THE WOMEN
WERE IN CONTROL, LEAVING VYTAS,
THE ONLY MALE OF THE TRIBE, ON
THE OUTSIDE LOOKING IN.
>> THERE'S ME AND THERE'S FIVE
GIRLS.
I'M THE ODD MAN OUT.
>> Jeff: OVER AT TADHANA, ARAS
THOUGHT HE WAS IN CONTROL.
>> I KNOW VYTAS WILL COME WITH
US.
I HAVE A REALLY DOMINANT
POSITION IN THE GAME
>> Jeff: BUT IT WAS TYSON WHO
WAS PULLING THE STRINGS,
GAG IDLE INFORMATION.
AND PUTTING TOGETHER A MAJORITY
ALLIANCE OF FIVE.
>> US FIVE.
AND THEN IT'S SMOOTH SAILING.
>> I'M GOOD FOR THAT.
>> HAPPY?
>> SOLID.
>> WE KNOW WE CAN TRUST EACH
OTHER BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE
ANYONE OVER THERE WE TRUST MORE.
>> Jeff: TYSON DOES IT!
TADHANA WINS IMMUNITY.
AFTER GALANG LOST THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE--
>> WE'VE DECIDE AS FOUR GIRLS
YOU'RE THE NEXT ONE TO GO.
>> LAURA B REVEALED THE WOMEN'S
PLAN, HOPING TO SPARE VYTAS'
FEELINGS.
>> I FELT LIKE I COULD TRUST
LAURA B., BUT NOW I JUST DON'T
KNOW.
>> Jeff: AND IN THE END, SHE
GOT HER WISH.
LAURA.
>> SAVING VYTAS' FEELINGS, BY
GETTING HERSELF VOTED OUT.
LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
10 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
>> WELL, THANKS FOR HAVING MY
BACK, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LIKE.
>> FEEL-- I DO FEEL SUCH TRUST
IN THIS GROUP.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HOW LUCKY ARE WE?
>> THAT BASED ON WHAT THE
NUMBERS ARE, THIS IS MY FIVE.
I'M SPEAKING FOR ARAS AS WELL.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS, WE'VE
GOT THIS THING TIGHT, IT'S
LOCKED.
>> YEAH.
>> SO YOU THINK THAT ARAS HAS
GERVASE 100% AND HE WON'T WAVER?
>> YUP.
>> I BELIEVE THAT, TOO.
>> OKAY.
>> AND THAT MAKES SIX, AND IT IT
GOES DOWN TOMORROW, THAT'S 11,
AND SIX IS THE MAJORITY, AND
THERE IS NOTHING ELSE THAT NEEDS
TO BE SAID.
THE MERGE IS COMING SOON.
AT THIS POINT, IT'S FIVE
TOGETHER NO MATTER WHAT.
WE'RE STANDING FOR A CERTAIN WAY
OF PLAYING THIS GAME.
WE'RE GOING TO BE MORAL.
WE'RE GOING TO BE HONEST.
EVEN IT MEANS OUR DEATH.
THAT'S NOT HOW I FEEL BUT THAT'S
WHAT I'M RAPPING TO THEM.
>> I THINK MONICA AT THIS POINT
HAD TO DO MORE TO STICK HER NECK
OUT FOR US THAN GERVASE HAS.
AND THAT WHEN IT GETS DOWN TO
FIVE AND SIX, THAT-- YOU KNOW,
WE'D PUT HER IN THAT FIVE SPOT
INSTEAD OF THE SIX SPOT.
>> I TOTALLY AGREE WITH THAT.
>> I THINK THAT LOYALTY SHOULD
BE REWARDED.
>> THAT MEANS A LOT, ESPECIALLY
COMING FROM YOU, TINA.
>> WELL, I DO MEAN IT.
>> THANK YOU.
WE JUST GOT BACK FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL, AND, YOU KNOW, TINA
MAKES AN ANNOUNCEMENT TONIGHT
THAT OKAY, GREAT, WE REALLY
APPRECIATE EVERYTHING YOU'RE
DOING, MONICA, AND YOU'RE NUMBER
FIVE.
>> WE'RE IN A PRETTY GOOD SPOT
AS LONG AS ARAS IS ON BOARD.
>> HE WILL BE.
>> IF WE MERGE, IT'S GOING TO BE
DIFFICULT WHEN PEOPLE COME TO ME
WITH AN OFFER BETTER THAN FIVE.
>> HEY, GUYS.
GUESS WHO?
>> HEY, WHO IS IT?
THE OTHER LAURA.
DAY 18.
I THEY WROTE DOWN LAURA B., AND
HERE I AM.
IT'S A HUGELY HORRIBLE
NONSTRATEGIC MOVE TO GET RID OF
ME AND KEEP VYTAS.
I THINK IT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> OH, MY GOSH.
THE GIRLS WERE ALL AGREEING TO
SEND VYTAS HOME.
>> THAT'S WHO I THOUGHT WAS GOG
WALK?
>> I'M TRYING TO BE A NICE,
HONEST PERSON, AND I TOLD HIM
HERE I AM.
AND THEY DIDN'T GO WITH THE PLAN
THAT I THOUGHT WE WERE DOING.
SO.
>> I WAS PRETTY SURE IT WAS
GOING TO BE VYTAS, TOO.
>> THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN THE
SMART MOVE.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
>> IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN VYTAS.
>> EXACTLY.
I DON'T FREAKING GET IT.
I DON'T GET IT.
I THINK IT'S A HUGE MISTAKE FOR
THOSE GIRLS TO LEAVE VYTAS IN
THE GAME.
THE MERGE, YOU KNOW, COULD BE
TOMORROW, AND HERE'S VYTAS
JOINING HIS BROTHER, JOINING ALL
THOSE GUYS.
THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE UP ON THE
THE GIRLS.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
RIDICULOUS.
>> OH, THIS IS ROUGH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD, HERE WE GO.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
"THE DAY IS HERE.
DO OUR DIE.
FOLLOWING TODAY'S DUEL, THE
WINNER WILL RE-ENTER THE GAME.
THE LOSERS WILL LEAVE THE GAME
FOR GOOD."
IT'S HAPPENING TODAY.
>> THIS FINAL DUEL IS THE ONLY
DUEL THAT REALLY MATTERS.
UN, ONE PERSON GOES BACK IN THE
GAME.
TWO PEOPLE GO HOME.
THIS FINAL DUEL IS WHAT I'VE
BEEN TRAINING FOR, FOR 12 DAYS.
I HAVE TO WIN THIS DUEL TODAY.
I'D BE DISAPPOINTED IN MYSELF.
CANDICE WOULD BE DISAPPOINTED IN
ME.
THERE IS NO OTHER WAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'LL MAKE THE
RICE.
>> I'M EITHER GOING TO GO HOME
TODAY.
MY GAME IS GOING TO BE OVER, OR
I'M GOING BACK IN IT.
NO SECOND PLACE IS GOOD ENOUGH
ANY MORE.
I HAVE TO WIN IF.
THIS IS IT.
AND IT'S JUST HARD BECAUSE I
TOLD MY DAUGHTER, I SAID I'D
COME BACK FOR YOU.
I HAVE TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE TO
GET BACK TO HER.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
TADHANA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW GLA TRIBE.
LAURA B. VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
JOHN.
LAURA M..
AND LAURA B.
WELCOME T TO REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA AND YOU'RE FINAL DUEL.
WHAT YOU HAVE DONE UP UNTIL NOW
DOES NOT MATTER IF YOU DON'T GET
IT DONE TODAY.
THE WINNER OF TODAY'S DUEL WILL
RE-ENTER THIS GAME.
DUEL WILL RE-ENTER THIS GAME,
CONTINUE-- YOUR QUEST FOR THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE
MILLION DOLLARS THAT GOES WITH
IT.
THE TWO LOSERS ARE OUT OF THIS
GAME FOR GOOD.
>> I HAVE MIXED FEELINGS ABOUT
MY MOOM COMING BACK IN THE GAME.
MY MOM, OBVIOUSLY, CREATED
RELATIONSHIPS OVER THERE THAT
WEREN'T THAT STRONG SO IT COULD
REALLY RUIN MY GAME IF SHE CAME
BACK.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET TO IT.
YOUR FINAL DUEL IS VERY SIMPLE.
YOU WILL HANG ON TO A POLE FOR
AS LONG AS YOU CAN.
ANY PART OF YOUR BODY TOUCHES
THE GROUND, YOU ARE OUT.
IT'S OVER.
LAST PERSON LEFT HANGING WINS
THIS DUEL, IS BACK IN THIS GAME,
AND WILL DECIDE WHO GETS THE
CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
THIS IS IT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY IS IN
POSITION, AND THIS DUEL IS ON.
>> I'M ALREADY SLIDING.
>> Jeff: LAURA B. IS
STRUGGLING RIGHT AWAY.
JUST FIND YOUR FOOTHOLD.
DON'T PANIC.
YOU'VE GOT LOTS OF FOOTHOLDS
BELOW YOU, TOO.
SECONDS INTO THE DUEL, LAURA B.
STRUGGLING, BUT NOW APPEARS TO
HAVE FOUND A SPOT.
THE RULE IS IF ANY PART OF YOUR
BODY TOUCHES THE GROUND, YOU'RE
OUT.
SO AS LONG AS YOUR FEET ARE NOT
TOUCHING, YOU'RE STILL IN, NO
MATTER HOW LOW YOU MAY GET.
JOHN KNOWS OF THIS DUEL BECAUSE
HIS WIFE, CANDICE, HAD IT IN
"HEROES VERSUS VILLAINS."
SO HE'S FAMILIAR WITH IT.
THE QUESTION IS WHO'S GOING TO
HOLD OUT THE LONGEST?
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: BEEN OUT HERE 20
MINUTES.
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO EARN THEIR
WAY BACK INTO THIS GAME.
JOHN'S STARTING TO SLIDE, HAS TO
FIND ANOTHER FOOTHOLD.
JOHN GOING TO KICK OFF HIS
SHOES, DESPERATE TO GET A
FOOTHOLD.
MAYBE THAT WILL HELP.
AND HE'S GOING TO WORK HIS WAY
BACK UP.
NOW THE SOCKS ARE SLIPPING.
THESE FOOTHOLDS ARE VERY NARROW.
YOU CAN'T GET YOUR WHOLE TOE ON
THERE.
IT DOESN'T TAKE LONG BEFORE IT
STARTS TO HURT.
JOHN IS FIGHTING NOW, AND IT
LOOKS LIKE HE MIGHT HAVE FOUND A
GOOD SPOT.
JOHN HAS RECOVERED.
LAURA M. HAS NOT MOVED.
LAURA B. NOT EVEN USING A
FOOTHOLD.
SHE IS LITERALLY JUST WRAPPED
AROUND IT LIKE A BABY HOLDING ON
TO HER MOM.
LAURA M. NOT MOVIN'.
CIERA QUIETLY WATCHING.
JOHN SLIDING DOWN ONCE AGAIN.
JOHN RIGHT NOW IS THE ONLY ONE
STRUGGLING.
AND HE'S SLIPPING MORE.
AND MORE.
JOHN IS OUT.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: NOTHING TO DO BUT LET
THE FRUSTRATION OUT.
>> GOOD JOB, JOHN.
>> Jeff: HE FOUGHT SO HARD FOR
SO MANY DAYS AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
IT IS NOW DOWN TO TWO WOMEN,
LAURA B., AND LAURA M..
BOTH WOMEN JUST WRAPPED AROUND
THE POLE.
LAURA B. SLOWLY BEGINNING TO
SLIDE.
>> OH, GOD.
>> Jeff: LAURA B. NOW DOWN TO
HER FINAL SECTION.
LAURA B. SLIPPING DOWN HER FINAL
FOOTHOLD.
SHE'S VERY CLOSE TO BEING OUT,
BUT SHE'S GOT ANOTHER GRIP.
IF YOU CAN HOLD THAT, YOU'RE
STILL IN IT.
BUT YOU CANNOT LET GO ANY MORE
OR YOU'LL BE OUT.
>> I'M NOT LETTING GO, LAURA B.
MY DAUGHTER'S ON THE LINE HERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO PRY MY
ARMS OFF OF THIS.
>> I'M JUST SLIDING.
>> Jeff: QUIT TELLING YOURSELF
YOU'RE SLIDING.
START TELLING YOURSELF YOU'RE
GLUE.
THE MORE YOU BELIEVE YOU CAN
HANG ON, THE LONGER YOU WILL
LAST.
LAURA B.'S LOCKED IN AGAIN.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
LAURA M. MOVING FOR THE FIRST
TIME.
LAURA M. STARTING TO SLIDE.
LAURA B. HANGING IN THERE, BUT
SHE'S STARTING TO SLIDE A LITTLE
MORE.
LAURA M. STRUGGLING TO GET A
FOOTHOLD.
>> DAMN IT.
>> Jeff: LAURA B. DESPERATELY
TRYING TO HANG ON.
INCHES AWAY.
LAURA B. IS OUT OF THIS GAME.
LAURA M. HAS EARNED HER WAY BACK
INTO THIS GAME.
YOU CAN COME DOWN.
>> I'M BARK I'M BACK, I'M BACK.
>> Jeff: LAURA B., VOTED
SECONDS INTO THIS GAME.
YOUR HUSBAND, RUPERT, TOOK YOUR
SPOT PUP GOT ANOTHER SHOT.
COULDN'T GET IT DONE.
AFTER 19 DAYS OUT HERE, WHAT
WILL YOU TAKE AWAY FROM THIS?
>> I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE I DEIFIED
THE ODDS.
I CAME OUT OF MY COMFORT ZONE
COMING HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE
AND PLAYING A SOCIAL GAME, WHICH
IS-- I'M A QUIET FARM GIRL.
AND I'M GOING TO GO BACK THE
STRONGEST WOMAN I'VE EVER BEEN
IN MY LIFE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAURA B.,
YOUR TIME IN THIS GAME IS DONE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
YOU CAN TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE
URN ON THE WAY OUT.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> I'LL LEAVE IT GRACEFULLY.
YOU GUYS TAKE CARE.
THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: JOHN, SHAKING YOUR
HEAD ALREADY.
>> DIDN'T WANT TO LEAVE, JEFF.
I WAS OUT ON REDEMPTION ISLAND
FOR 12 DAYS THINKING ABOUT THIS
CHALLENGE RIGHT HERE.
IT'S JUST TOUGH TO END THIS WAY.
>> Jeff: CAN YOU COMPARE THIS
TO SOME OF THE TOUGH THINGS
PROBABLY, YOU KNOW, SOME OF THE
THINGS I HAD TO GO THROUGH MY
FIRST YEAR AT WEST POINT, ALWAYS
ON EDGE.
AND THIS IS PROBABLY THE HARDEST
19 DAYS I'VE-- I'VE EXPERIENCED.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
>> YEAH.
THE SILVER LINING IF NOT FOR MY
BLINDSIDE I WOULDN'T HAVE SPENT
ANY DAYS WITH HER OUT HERE IN
THE GAME AND I GOT TO SPEND TWO
DAYS IN REDEMPTION ISLAND.
THIS WAS A LOT HARDER THAN I
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
>> Jeff: JOHN, AFTER 19 DAYS--
I KNOW IT'S A DISAPPOINTMENT--
YOUR TIME IN THIS GAME IS OVER.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
PUT YOUR BUFF IN THE URNSPD ON
THE WAY OUT.
>> GOOD JOB, JOHN.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: LAURA M., HOW DOES IT
FEEL?
>> GOOD.
I'M STILL IN THE GAME, LIKE IT
SHOULD BE.
AND THAT'S THE GLORY OF IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAURA,
BEFORE YOU OFFICIALLY RE-ENTER
THE GAME, YOU AND EVERYBODY ELSE
CAN DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE MERGED.
>> WHOO-HOO.
>> Jeff: I'LL LET YOU PASS
THESE OUT, LAURA.
DROP YOUR OLD ONE PUT ON YOUR
NEW TRIBE COLOR.
>> AND IT SMELLS GOOD!
>> I TOLD YOU I'D BE BACK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ONE MORE
BIT OF BUSINESS.
BECAUSE YOU WON THE DUEL, ARE
YOU IN CHARGE OF WHO GETS THE
CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
NOW, THE LAST SEVERAL HAVE BEEN
TOSSED RIGHT IN THE FIRE.
BUT GIVEN THAT WE ARE NOW
MERGED, MAYBE THIS HAS MORE
VALUE.
BEFORE YOU DECIDE ANYTHING, YOU
CAN GIVE THIS TO ANYBODY YOU
WANT WHO IS STILL IN THE GAME.
THAT NOW INCLUDES YOU.
I HAVE A FEELING THIS IS GOING
TO JOIN THE OTHERS IN THE FIRE.
ALL RIGHT, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> GLAD WE MADE IT.
>> AS IT STANDS NOW, MY STRATEGY
IS TO GO GALANG STRONG, THE
ORIGINAL GALANG, ME, GERVASE,
TYSON, MONCARKS TINA, PLUS VYTAS
AND KATIE.
THAT'S SEVEN.
THERE ARE 11 PEOPLE IN THE GAME.
WE HAVE A DISTINCT ADVANTAGE.
>> WHERE'S THE FOOD!
>> RED WINE!
>> SHOULD WE SET IT OUT?
>> LET'S SET IT ALL OUT.
>> YEAH, I WANT ONE OF THOSE
SALAMI SANDWICHES.
>> YEAH, GIRL.
>> WE HIT THE BEACH.
WE HAVE A PICNIC, THE MERGE
FEAST.
THERE'S WINE AND CHEESE AND
CRACKERS AND SALAMI.
AND I'M STUFFING MY FACE, BUT
THE WHOLE TIME I'M REALLY
THINKING, OKAY, WHAT CAN I DO
HERE TO MAKE SURE I STAY IN THE
NUMBERS?
>> CAN I HAVE A SALAMI, PLEASE?
>> OH, MY GOD, I'M SO HAPPY.
>> I CAN'T HANDLE A WHOLE LOT OF
SALAMI.
>> WE HAD FIVE SOILED, ME,
CALEB, TYSON, GERVASE, AND
CIERA.
AND NOW I'M THINKING, OKAY, IS
LAURA M. GOING TO COME WITH
CIERA OR IS LAURA M. GOING TO
PULL CIERA.
LAURA M., KATIE, AND IT COULD
HINGE ON LAURA.
ONCE THE MERGE HAMS, THIS IS
WHEN THE GAME STARTS.
THIS IS WHERE SURVIVOR REALLY
BECOMES SURVIVOR.
>> LAURA, HOW LONG COULD YOU
HAVE HUNG ON UP THERE?
>> FOREVER.
>> YOU WEREN'T TIRED AT ALL?
YOU DIDN'T LOOK LIKE YOU WERE.
>> MY THIGHS WERE HOLDING ON SO
HARD TO THAT THING.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 19 DAYS I
GET TO PLAY WITH MY DAUGHTER.
MY PLAN IS US COUPLES HAVE TO
STAY TOGETHER.
THAT'S SIX RIGHT THERE.
I DEFINITELY DO NEED TO TALK TO
CIERA.
I HAVE A LOT OF WORK TO DO, A
LOT OF WORK TO DO, BUT I'M STILL
HERE AND I'M NOT GIVING UP.
>> LET'S START MAKING THE FLAG.
>> AND MAYBE WE SHOULD COME UP
WITH A NAME.
>> LET'S GO FOR A WALK.
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO EXPECT IT
ANYWAY.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO DOWN THE
BEACH?
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE HER DOWN
THE BEACH.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SHOW HER THE GROUNDS.
>> IT ALL COMES DOWN TO LAURA M.
>> I KNOW.
>> AS LONG AS CIERA IS WORKING
HER.
>> I THINK SO.
WE'LL KEEP IN TOUCH WITH THEM.
>> LET'S GO DOWN ONE MORE.
>> OKAY.
>> PLAYING WITH YOUR LOVED ONE,
AND THEN MAKING IT TO THE MERGE,
I FEEL SO BLESSED.
BUT THEN THERE'S ALSO THE FACT
THAT MY MOM CAUSED SOME RIFFS
AND HAD SOME ENEMIES, CLEARLY,
BECAUSE THEY VOTED HER OUT.
AND IT'S ALL SHIFTED, AND WITH
MY MOM COME BACK IN THE GAME, IT
COULD REALLY HURT ME.
SO WHERE DO I START?
SO HERE'S WHAT'S HAPPENED.
I'M IN AN ALLIANCE.
>> WITH-- PLEASE TELL ME CALEB
AND HAYDEN.
>> YES.
>> OH, GOOD.
>> HERE'S WHERE IT GETS SKETCHY.
YOU MAKE IT A LITTLE SKETCHY AND
HERE'S WHY.
BECAUSE IT WAS AN ALLIANCE
FORMED ON BEAM POOEM WITHOUT
LOVED ONES.
IT'S ME, CADEN, TYSON AND
GERVASE.
AND WE PROMISED IECH OTHER FINAL
FIVE.
DON'T TALK STRATEGY WITH
ANYBODY, NO ONE.
>> OKAY.
>> SO HERE'S THE THING, ARAS IS
NEXT TO GO.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE MY MOM IS ON
BOARD AND REALLY UNDERSTANDS HOW
WE'RE GOING TO PLAY IT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M THE TEACHER YOU,
YOU KNOW, TEACHING MY MOM THE
WAYS, THE WAYS OF THE TRIBE.
DON'T TOWK TAANYONE.
>> ME AND CIERA ARE THE PEOPLE
THAT ARE GOING TO DECIDE WANT
FATE OF EITHER THE COUPLES OR
THE FATE OF THE SINGLES.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT HERE
I WAS ON REDEMPTION ISLAND
THINKING THE GAME IS OVER, AND
NOW I'M IN A POWER POSITION IN
THIS GAME OF WHO'S GOING TO GO
HOME?
>> JUST DON'T PLAY HARD.
>> YOU GOING FOR A WALK, TYS?
>> YEAH.
OKAY, I'LL BE BACK.
YOU GOTTA ACT FAST COME MERGE
TIME, SO NOW THE ONLY FACTOR IN
THE GAME IS FINDING OUT WHERE
THE IMMUNITY IDOLS ARE.
WHEN THE TRIBE SWAP HAPPENED,
HAYDEN GAVE ME ALL THE INFO HE
KNEW ABOUT THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
I'M PRETTY SURE IT'S AT THE
GIANT TREE ON THE WAY TO THE
WATERFALL.
OKAY.
THIS HAS TO BE THE SERPENT TREE.
THIS IS THE SERPENT.
SO MAYBE IF I DIG UNDERNEATH IT
OVER HERE.
TA-DA!
I'M DEFINITELY NOT SHARING THIS
WITH ANYBODY ELSE RIGHT NOW.
IF IT WORKS TO MY ADVANTAGE TO
SHARE IT WITH SOMEBODY IN MY
ALLIANCE TO PUSH SOMEBODY ELSE
OUT, THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO, BUT
RIGHT NOW, NOBODY NEEDS TO KNOW
I HAVE IT.
I STEPPED ON THAT PROBABLY LIKE
20 TIMES.
LET'S SEE HOW SWEET IT IS.
I HOPE IT'S SOILED GOLD.
TRY IT ON.
MAKE SURE IT FITS.
HOORAY.
I HAVE NEVER HAD AN IDOL BEFORE
AND I'VE ALSO NEVER WON THE SHOW
BEFORE.
DO THOSE CORRELATE DIRECTLY WITH
ONE ANOTHER?
PROBABLY NOT, BUT AT LEAST THIS
IS A LITTLE MORE ADVANTAGE.
>> GOOD JOB, DUDE, YOU MADE IT.
YOU MADE THE MERGE.
>> SKIN OF MY TEETH, BRO.
>> I KNEW YOU WOULD.
>> I'M SO STOKED I GET TO PLAY
WITH ARAS.
HE IS MY BROTHER AND I LOVE HIM
AND I WANT TO GO DEEP IN THIS
GAME WITH HIM.
DUDE, WE HAVE A PATH AND IT IS
SO PERFECT.
>> IT IS SO PERFECT.
>> TINA AND KATIE, WE'RE SO IN
THERE.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND MONICA, EVEN THOUGH SHE
TALKS A LOT AND GETS AROUND, I
TOTALLY THINK SHE'S ON BOARD ITW
IT.
>> I THINK SO, TOO,.
>> AND WITH YOU AND GERKS RV.
>> AND TYSON IS OUR SEVEN.
>> DO WE EVEN NEED THE NOOED
THAT?
>> YEAH, WE DO.
TYSON-- DEFINITELY KEEP TYSON
AROUND.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT IF HE GOES ON A RUN?
>> HE CAN'T.
HE'S GOT A BROKEN ARM.
>> WE LAID OUT OUR PLAN FOR THE
SEVEN-- TEEN AMONG GERVAS TYSON,
JRVE, AND ARAS AND MYSELF.
THERE ARE SEVEN OF US.
>> I DON'T TRUST LAURA M. AT ALL
I THINK SHE'S THE SCARIEST
PERSON IN THE GAME RIGHT NOW.
GETTING RID OF LAURA IS NOT
BECAUSE SHE WAS ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND AND BACK, BUT SHE IS THE
SAFEST PLAY.
EVERYONE FEELS UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH HER.
>> IF PEOPLE WERE SMART, THEY
WOULD MOBILIZE AGAINST US RIGHT
AWAY.
BUT THEY'RE NOT GOING TO.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO GET
LAURA OR CIERA.
>> "BLOOD VERSUS WATER" SHOULD
IN THE END BE CALLED VYTAS
VERSUS ARAS BECAUSE WE WOULD BE
STUPID RIGHT NOW NOT TO GET TO
THE END.
>> YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> YES.
HERE'S WHAT THEY'RE TELLING ME.
THEY'RE TELLING ME THAT I'M
NUMBER 5 AND MONICA'S HAPPY TO
MAKE IT TO 5 BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T
HAVE A CHANCE IN HELL IN
WINNING.
>> OKAY, SO HERE'S WHAT I HAVE
SET UP.
>> OKAY.
>> ME AND GERVASE ARE TIGHT.
>> BUT IS HE GOING TO FLIP
BECAUSE GERVASE THINKS HE'S
FINAL THREE WITH ARAS AND TINA?
>> NO.
I NEED TO TELL MONICA ABOUT THE
PLAN TO GET ARAS OUT BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE TO SHOW HER A
LITTLE LOVE.
YOU HAVE TO SHOW HER SOME
RESPECT.
JUST TO SOLIDIFY THE NUMBERS.
YOU'RE WITH US.
THAT'S THE MAJORITY.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO STICK
WITH.
WE TAKE ARAS OUT FIRST AND THEN
START PLUCKING THEM OFF ONE BY
ONE.
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS--
>> HERE'S THE THING.
>> SHE JUST LIKES TO REPEAT THE
SAME IDEA OVER AND OVER AND OVER
AGAIN, AND I DON'T WANT TO BE
RUDE TO HER BECAUSE I NEED TO
KEEP HER CLOSE.
>> THE ONLY OTHER OPTION IS--
>> AT SOME POINT YOU JUST HAVE
TO BE, LIKE, "MONICA, SHUT UP."
>> ARE YOU SURE THAT GERVASE IS
WITH YOU?
>> I'M SURE GERVASE IS WITH ME.
>> YOU'RE SURE.
>> I'M SURE.
I'M JUST LIKE
( SIZE )
GIVE ME A RUSTY SPOON SO I CAN
DIG BOTH MY EYEBALLS OUT AND TRY
AND JAM IT THROUGH MY EYE SOCKET
INTO MY BRAIN.
IT'S TAKING ALL OF MY PATIENCE,
ALL OF IT.
>> I WANT TO KNOW WHERE ARE YOU
WITH ME.
>> WE'RE ANYTHING TO THE END.
>> OKAY.
THIS WAS OUR THING FROM THE
BEGINNING.
>> FROM THE BEGINNING.
ME, YOU, AND GERVASE.
>> LISTEN, I'LL FILL YOU IN.
I HAD A REALITY SANDWICH THAT IT
WAS BASICALLY SPELLED OUT,
MONICA, I'M JUST GOING TO TELL
YOU LIKE IT IS.
YOU'RE NUMBER FIVE.
>> RIGHT.
>> IF TYSON WOULD JUST SAY, "I'M
100% WITH YOU," I WOULD PROBABLY
JUMP IN BED WITH THE WHOLE IDEA
AND RELAX, BUT THEN AGAIN, IT'S
"SURVIVOR."
HOW CAN YOU RELAX?
I'M NOT SURE.
I'M IN A BIG PREDICAMENT.
>> JUST KEEP PLAYING ALONG.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
LAURA M., I'LL TAKE BACK THE
IDOL.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NO MORE.
THIS IS WHAT YOU COVET NOW.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY NECKLACE
WITH THIS AROUND YOUR NECK, YOU
ARE SAFE AT THE VOTE.
YOU CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
WITHOUT IT, ARE YOU VULNERABLE.
SHALL WE GET TO IT.
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, WE'RE GOING TO TEST
YOUR MEMORY.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU A SERIES
OF SYMBOLS.
YOU'RE GOING TO REPEAT THEM BACK
TO ME USING YOUR CUBE.
YOU GET IT RIGHT, YOU STAY
ALIVE.
YOU GET IT WRONG, ARE YOU OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, ONE OF YOU WILL BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
FIRST ITEM, BARREL.
CRATE.
CANNON.
SHIP.
COMPASS.
LANTERN.
NOW I'M GOING TO ASK YOU TO
REPEAT THEM BACK TO ME.
SHOW ME THE FIRST ITEM.
EVERYBODY HAS BARREL.
CORRECT ANSWER, BARREL.
EVERYBODY'S RIGHT.
NEXT ITEM.
EVERYBODY HAS CRATE EXCEPT FOR
MONICA.
CORRECT ANSWER IS CRATE.
MONICA HAS IT WRONG.
MONICA YOU'RE THE FIRST OUT.
SET YOUR CUBE DOWN.
HAVE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
FIND THE NEXT ITEM, AND REVEAL.
EVERYBODY HAS CANNON, EXCEPT FOR
CALEB AND KATIE.
THEY BOTH HAVE COMPASS.
CORRECT ANSWER IS, CANNON.
CALEB IS OUT, KATIE IS OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
>> LOSER.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY ELSE KEEP
GOING.
FIND YOUR NEXT ITEM.
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
EVERYBODY HAS SHIP, EXCEPT FOR
TYSON, AND TINA, THEY BOTH HAVE
COMPASS.
THE CORRECT ANSWER IS SHIP.
TINA IS OUT.
TYSON IS OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
NEXT ITEM, REVEAL.
EVERYBODY HAS COMPASS, EXCEPT
HAYDEN, WHO HAS LANTERN.
CORRECT ANSWER, COMPASS.
HAYDEN HAS IT WRONG.
HAYDEN IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
NOT EVEN THROUGH THE FIRST ROUND
AND WE'VE LOST MORE THAN HALF OF
THE TRIBE.
SHOW ME THE LAST ITEM IN THIS
ROUND.
EVERYBODY HAS LANTERN.
CORRECT ANSWER, LANTERN.
LAURA MOVES ON, CIERA MOVES ON,
VYTAS MOVES ON, RATS MOVES ON,
AND GERVASE MOVES ON.
>> GOOD JOB, BABE.
>> Jeff: NEXT ROUND.
WE'RE GOING TO GO TO SEVEN ITEMS
NOW.
FIRST ITEM, BARREL.
LANTERN.
CANNON.
COMPASS.
BARREL.
CANNON.
A LOT OF ITEMS.
YOU'RE NOW GOING TO REPEAT THEM
BACK TO ME.
SHOW ME THE FIRST ITEM.
EVERYBODY HAS BARREL.
THE CORRECT ANSWER, BARREL.
EVERYBODY'S RIGHT.
REVEAL THE NEXT ITEM.
EVERYBODY HAS LANTERN EXCEPT
LAURA, WHO HAS CANNON.
CORRECT ANSWER, LANTERN.
LAURA IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
NEXT ITEM, REVEAL.
VYTAS, ARAS, AND GERVASE ALL
HAVE CANNON.
CIERA HAS COMPASS.
WHO'S RIGHT?
CORRECT ANSWER, CANNON.
CIERA IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH NEXT TO
YOUR MOM.
>> GOOD LUCK, BOYS.
>> Jeff: AND WITH THAT WE ARE
DOWN TO THREE.
ONE PAIR OF BROTHERS, VYTAS AND
ARAS, ONE INDIVIDUAL, GERVASE.
SHOW ME THE NEXT ITEM.
EVERYBODY HAS LANTERN.
YOU'RE ALL THREE RIGHT.
NEXT ITEM.
VYTAS AND ARAS HAVE COMPASS.
GERVASE, BEFORE I EVEN SHOW IT,
FEELS HE'S WRONG.
GERVASE SHOWS CRATE.
YOU'RE SECOND GUESSING YOURSELF?
>> I KNOW I'M WRONG.
>> Jeff: YOU KNOW YOU'RE
WRONG?
>> YOU'RE CORRECT, YOU ARE
WRONG.
IT IS COMPASS.
GERVASE IS OUT.
ARAS AND VYTAS STAY ALIVE.
THE TWO BROTHERS ARE SHOWING
DOWN.
THEY'VE HAD A COMPETITION THEIR
ENTIRE LIFE.
IT'S PLAYING OUT AGAIN ON
"SURVIVOR."
SHOW ME THE NEXT ITEM.
BOTH SHOW BARREL.
CORRECT ITEM, BARREL.
SHOW ME THE NEXT ITEM.
VYTAS HOLDS UP QUICKLY.
ARAS TAKING HIS TIME.
VYTAS SHOWS CANNON, ARAS SHOWS
LANTERN.
ONE IS RIGHT, ONE IS NOT.
ONE HAS JUST WON IMMUNITY.
ONE HAS LOST.
CORRECT ANSWER, CANNON.
ARAS IS OUT.
VYTAS WINS IMMUNITY.
SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
( APPLAUSE )
>> GREAT JOB, GUYS!
>> Jeff: CONGRATULATIONS.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY FOR VYTAS,
SAFE AT TONIGHT'S VOTE.
UNFORTUNATELY, FOR THE REST OF
YOU, AFTER 21 DAYS, SOMEBODY
FROM THIS GROUP OF REMAINING 10
WILL BE VOTED OUT, SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
SHOULD BE A VERY INTERESTING
AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> GOOD JOB.
( APPLAUSE )
>> YEAH, V.!
>> THE BATTLE OF THE BROTHERS,
ONCE AGAIN.
>> IN YOU NEED IMMUNITY IN THIS
GAME YOU ALREADY HAVE MADE A FEW
MISTAKES AND I'M MAKING SURE I
AM NOT GOING INTO A CHALLENGE
NEEDING IMMUNITY.
I DIDN'T NEED IMMUNITY TODAY BUT
I NEEDED TO BEAT MY BROTHER, AND
IT HAPPENED SO I'M HAPPY.
>> IT LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> MATCHES YOUR SHORTS.
>> MOVING FORWARD THE BIGGEST
THREAT IN THE GAME IS ARAS AND
I.
WE HAVE THIS BEACH LOCKED, AND I
WOULD BE SURPRISED IF ANYBODY
HAS THE GUTS TO DO ANYTHING
ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T TRUST LAURA M..
WE GOTTA GET HER OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> SO YOU GUYS, YOU THREE ARE
GONNA VOTE GERVASE?
>> AND THEN ALL THE BOYS ARE
GONNA VOTE LAURA M.
>> RIGHT NOW WE HAVE NINE PIECES
WORKING SOMEWHAT IN UNISON.
EVERYONE THINKS THEY'RE WITH US.
ALL THE BOYS ARE VOTING FOR
LAURA M..
TINA, MONCARKS AND KATIE VOTING
FOR CIERA.
IN CASE LAURA M. HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, IT GETS FLUSHED
AND CIERA GOES HOME.
AND IF NOT, THEN LAURA M. GOES
HOME.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE ALL INTENDING?
ALL RIGHT.
AND ARE YOU OKAY WITH IT?
>> YEAH.
IT'S A GAME.
>> HERE'S WHAT I'M SCARED ABOUT.
>> DO YOU THINK ARAS HAS THE
IDOL?
>> AND HERE'S THE ONLY REASON I
SAY THAT BECAUSE ON MY SEASON
LAST TIME, RUSSELL HAD IT.
>> NO, NO, WAIT.
HE'S SO COMFORTABLE RIGHT NOW.
>> ARAS?
>> IS HE COMFORTABLE BECAUSE HE
HAS AN IDOL?
>> IN MY EVERYDAY LIFE, I'M MY
MOM'S BIGGEST CHEERLEADER, GO,
MOM, GO, MOM.
THAT'S MY NATURAL INSTINCT.
BUT MY GAME SIDE IS SAYING,
OKAY, LAURA, THINK ABOUT.
BMAYOU'RE DOING.
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY WE THROW FOUR
VOTES-- HEAR ME OUT-- TO LAURA
AND THREE TO ARAS.
HERE'S WHY.
WE GO TO TRIBAL, AND LET'S SAY
WE GO AND ARAS PULLS OUT THE
IDOL.
>> IT'S THE WEIRDEST THING.
I'VE NEVER FELT IT BEFORE.
IT'S A STRUGGLE.
AND I WANT TO LISTEN TO MY MOM,
DO WHAT MY MOM SAYS.
BUT ON THE SAME HAND, I'M HERE
TO PLAY MY GAME.
>> THROW FOUR TINA'S WAY, THREE
ARAS' WAY.
ARAS PLAYS THE IDOL.
TINA'S OUT OF THE GAME.
NOW WE HAVE EVEN MORE NUMBERS.
>> IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE ARAS HAS
THE PLAN, WHICH IS THE MEN ARE
ALL GOING TO VOTE FOR LAURA, AND
ALL THE GIRLS ARE GOING TO VOTE
FOR CIERA.
>> LET ME GRAB ONE OF THOSE.
>> WE'RE GOOD STILL.
>> THAT'S COOL.
>> THE PLAN WITH TYSON IS THAT
ME, TYSON, MONICA, HAYDEN,
CALEB, CIERA, AND LAURA M.VOTE
FOR ARAS.
>> YOU GO WITH THE PLAN.
>> KING ARAS.
>> SIR ARAS.
>> IT JUST STARTS TO GET A
LITTLE TRICKY NOW BECAUSE I'M
NOT SO SURE THAT EVERYBODY IS ON
THE SAME PAGE BECAUSE PEOPLE CAN
SAY ONE THING TO YOUR FACE BUT
BEHIND YOUR BACK THEY COULD SAY
WHATEVER ELSE.
I JUST CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HOW IT
ALL SHAKES OUT.
I THINK I HAVE-- AND I KNOW HOW
IT WAS GOING TO FALL OUT PUT I
COULD BE TOTALLY WRONG, WHICH IS
THE CRAZY PART ABOUT THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: SO, TYSON, LET ME SEE
IF I CAN SET THIS UP.
WE MERGE.
WE HAVE THE ORIGINAL TRIBAL
LINES.
WE HAVE THE NEW TRIBAL LINES
FROM THE SWITCH.
AND-- TOP OF ALL OF THIS,
THERE'S BLOOD VERSUS WATER.
IN THIS CASE THREE, PAIRS OF
TRUE BLOOD.
>> CORRECT.
AND I'M SURE THE COUPLES WANT TO
WORK TOGETHER AS FAR AS THEY
CAN.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE SURE?
>> WELL, IF MY BROTHER WERE
HERE, I'D WANT TO WORK WITH HIM
AS LONG AS I COULD.
>> Jeff: ARAS, IS THAT A FAIR
STATEMENT?
>> IT'S ABSOLUTELY FAIR.
BUT RIGHT NOW, THERE ARE 11
PEOPLE HERE.
THAT MEANS SIX PEOPLE HAVE TO
COME TOGETHER TONIGHT.
VYTAS AND I CAN'T JUST TRUST
EACH OTHER AND BE LIKE, COOL,
WE'RE FINE.
WE HAVE TO FIND FOUR OTHER
PEOPLE WHO WE REALLY TROWFT GET
THE MAJORITY IN THIS VOTE
TONIGHT SO I THINK IT'S MORE
ABOUT MAKING RELATIONSHIPS WITH
EVERYONE THAN JUST VYTAS AND I.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, IF WE LOOK AT
THE NUMBERS, THERE ARE THREE
PAIRS OF LOVED ONES-- THAT WOULD
BE SIX-- AND THERE ARE FIVE
INDIVIDUALS.
THE ONLY HICCUP TO THAT IS ONE
OF THOSE PAIRS INVOLVES LAURA
WHO WAS VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME
AND JUST GOT BACK IN, AND IF YOU
LOOK AT THE HISTORY OF
"SURVIVOR" THAT PERSON OFTEN IS
VOTED OUT AT THE VERY FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHICH WOULD BE
TONIGHT.
>> THERE'S NO DOUBT, JEFF.
IN PAST SEASONS YOU COME OFF
REDEMPTION, YOU TEND TO HEAD
RIGHT BACK.
>> Jeff: DOES THAT POTENTIALLY
MAKE LAURA AND CIERA SWING VOTES
BECAUSE SHE MAY NOT BE WELCOMED
BACK IN THIS GAME?
>> SURE, AND NOT JUST LAURA AND
CIERA.
YOU HAVE TO ASSUME THE PAIRS ARE
GOING TO WORK TOGETHER SO ANY
ONE OF THE PAIRS COULD
POTENTIALLY BE A SWING.
>> Jeff: KATIE, WHY WOULD THAT
MAKE SENSE IF YOU AND YOUR MOM
COULD MOVE OVER TO THE
INDIVIDUAL SIDE AND MAKE IT A
7-4 GAME.
>> RIGHT NOW I DON'T KNOW WHO
FIT WOULD.
WE CAME INTO THE MERGE WITH AN
IDEA WHO WE WANT TO WORK WITH
AND I DON'T WANT TO COMPLICATE
ANYTHING RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: KATIE IS BASICALLY
SAYING, NOT SO MUCH.
I'M GOING TO STICK WITH THE
LOVED ONES AND IF THAT'S TRUE,
AND LAURA AND CIERA BITE ON
THAT, IT'S GAME OVER FOR THE
INDIVIDUALS.
>> RIGHT, IT'S DEFINITELY A
THREATENING THING TO SEE THERE
ARE SIX OF THEM AND FIVE
INDIVIDUALS BUT YOU COULD DO
THAT WITH THE GUYS, TOO.
THERE ARE SIX GUYS AND FIVE
GIRLS.
IN THE END, IT'S WHO YOU TRUST
THE MOST.
IF YOU TRUST THE PAIR THE MOST,
YOU GO WITH THEM.
IF NOT, YOU FIND A DIFFERENT
ROAD.
SO THERE ARE A LOT OF DIFFERENT
WAYS YOU COULD CUT PIE, AND I
HOPE TO GET THE LARGEST PORTION
OF THE PIE, JEFF.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: LAURA, WHAT'S YOUR
BEST PLAY RIGHT NOW?
KNOWING THAT YOU HAVE A TARGET
ON YOUR BACK SIMPLY BECAUSE YOU
WERE ALREADY VOTED OUT ONCE?
>> YEAH, IT'S LIKE THE KID
THAT'S BEEN HOME SICK WITH
CHICKEN POX FOR THE LAST TWO
WEEKS AND YOU FINALLY COME TO
SCHOOL AND NOBODY WANTS TO PLAY
WITH YOU.
THE ADVANTAGE OF HAVING A LOVED
ONE HERE IS THE STUFF I CAN
FILTER THROUGH CIERA.
SHE A GREAT SOCIAL PLAYER.
I LOVE THE FACT THEY CAN GO TO
MY DAUGHTER AND SAY, "CIERA, I
NEED ADVICE."
AND MY DAUGHTER IS PUTTING ME IN
CHECK.
IT'S AMAZING.
>> Jeff: CIERA, IS THAT A ROLE
REVERSAL OR IS THAT HOW IT'S
ALWAYS BEEN?
>> NO OORKTS A TOTAL REVERSAL
OUT HERE.
IT'S FUNNY, I'LL FIND MYSELF
BEING LIKE, "MOM, RELAX."
"LET'S JUST ENJOY OURSELVES."
AND SHE'LL LOOK AT ME, "WHAT DO
I DO?"
AND I SAY, "JUST CALM DOWN
BECAUSE YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT."
>> Jeff: GERVASE WHAT, DO YOU
THINK WILL BE DIFFERENT AFTER
TONIGHT'S VOTE.
>> I THINK FOR THE SMART
PLAYERS, NOTHING.
IT'S FOOLISH TO ACT CRAZY.
YOU HAVE TO STAY CALM EVERY
SECOND OF EVERY MINUTE OF EVERY
HOUR AFFECTS THIS GAME.
IT COULD CHANGE LIKE THAT.
SO YOU HAVE TO BE READY WHEN IT
DOES.
AND TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
CALEB, YOU'RE UP.
>> WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS SINCE THE
BEGINNING, BUT I'M SORRY.
>> THIS IS MY POWER MOVE IN THIS
GAME.
I LOVE YOU LIKE A BROTHER, BUT
IT'S JUST HOW IT IS.
>> I VOTED YOU DOWN ONCE.
I MIGHT AS WELL VOTE YOU DOWN
TWICE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY TNOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO
DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LAURA.
LAURA.
CIERA.
TWO VOTES LAURA, TWO VOTES CIERA
ARAS.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES LAURA, TWO
VOTES SKIER ATWO VOTES ARAS.
ARAS.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ARAS.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES ARAS.
TWO VOTES LAURA, TWO VOTES
CIERA.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VERSUS WATER,"
ARAS.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH PUP NEED TO BRING
ME YOUR TORCH.
>> WELL PLAYED GUYS.
WELL PLAYED.
HAVE LOTS OF FUN, OKAY.
>> LOVE YOU, BUDDY.
>> LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: ARAS, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
>> SEE YOU GUYS.
HAVE FUN.
>> Jeff: WELL, ALTHOUGH THERE
WERE QUESTIONS COMING INTO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, THERE'S
CERTAINLY A LITTLE CLARITY NOW
THAT IT'S OVER.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> BRAVO, BRAVO, YOU HAVE FIVE
JURY VOTES YOU'LL NEVER GET
EXPWHRT GAME GETS UGLY.
>> VENGEANCE IS GOING TO BE MINE
AT SOME POINT.
>> Jeff: JUST WHEN YOU THOUGHT
IT COULDN'T GET NEWSCAST YEAR.
THERE'S A FOOD EATING
COMPETITION.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I'M STILL SHOCKED A LITTLE
BIT.
THE FIRST TIME I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR" I NEVER GOT VOTED
OUT.
SO TO GET VOTED OUT WAS A NEW
EXPERIENCE FOR ME.
I THINK THE BIGGEST PAIN FOR ME
IS VYTAS IS IN A REALLY TOUGH
POSITION NOW.
I KNOW VYTAS IS IN A REALLY
TOUGH POSITION.
I WOULDN'T BE SHOCKED IF HE IS
THE ONE WHO JOINS ME HERE IN
TWOOR THREE NIGHTS.