>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR".
>> LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AFTER LAURA M. WAS VOTED OUT, NO
COUPLES WERE LEFT AND THE GAME
WAS ON.
>> THE FOUR OF US.
>> Jeff: CALEB AND HAYDEN SAW
A CHANCE TO BLIND SIDE THEIR
BIGGEST THREAT.
>> TYSON'S GOT A HELL OF A
RESUME TO PREACH TO THE JURY
WHEN WE GET THERE.
>> Jeff: AFTER CIERA REVEALED
THEIR PLAN --
>> HE SAID "WE WANT TYSON GONE."
>> Jeff: TYSON WAS READY TO
FIGHT FIRE WITH FIRE.
>> I NEED CALEB AND HAYDEN OUT.
>> Jeff: NICING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, CALEB AND HAYDEN FEARED
THEIR PLAN WAS FALLING APART.
>> CIERA SAID YOU GUYS WANTED ME
GO.
>> BECAUSE WE THOUGHT YOU WERE
TRYING TO GET US.
>> Jeff: SO THEY THROUGH CIERA
UNDER THE BUS.
>> IT'S GOT TO BE CIERA.
>> ON THE SAME PAGE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
TYSON INSURED HIS SAFETY BY
PLAYING HIS IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR TYSON WILL
NOT COUNT.
IN THE END HE DIDN'T NEED IT
WHEN CALEB WAS SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
CALEB, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SIX ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
>> WE'RE ALL HERE FOR DAY 30.
>> PIT OF SNAKES.
I'M SO EXCITED.
>> GOOD MOVE.
NOBODY SAW IT COMING.
>> SORRY, DUDE.
>> THAT'S A GREAT MOVE, MAN.
TRIBAL COUNCIL BLEW UP IN OUR
FACE BUT WE WERE EXPECTING TO
BLIND SIDE CIERA BUT GOSH!
IT WAS JUST -- I MEAN, GOOD MOVE
TO THEM.
KAT WOULD SAY TOUCHE AND I'M
THINKING THESE SONS OF -- GUNS.
(LAUGHS)
I HOPE EVERYBODY HERE LIKES
SECOND PLACE.
BECAUSE IF TYSON GOES TO THE END
HE'S WINNING BECAUSE HE IS
PLAYING A HELL OF A GAME.
PURE POETRY.
YOU ARE PLAYING THE BEST GAME.
NOBODY CAN TOUCH YOU SO FAR.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY!
OH, NO!
TYSON CAN'T DO NOTHING IF IT
WASN'T FOR ME!
TYSON WOULDN'T BE WHERE HE'S AT!
>> COME ON, LET THIS GUY TALK!
>> HE'S NOT PLAYING THIS GAME!
I'M PLAYING HIS GAME.
I GOT MY HAND ON HIS BACK.
>> HE'S PULLING THE TRIGGER.
>> HE'S ON MY LAP!
GERVASE, IF YOU'RE SITTING NEXT
TO HIM IN TEND HE'LL BEAT YOU
ALL DAY.
SAME WITH EVERYBODY HERE.
>> HAYDEN, WHY ARE YOU THROWING
ME UNDER THE BUS, DUDE?
>> I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
IT'S THE FLAT OUT TRUTH.
YOU DESERVE TO WIN THE GAME.
>> I DIDN'T LIKE HOW HAYDEN
THREW ME UNDER THE BUS WHEN HE
SAID "I'M VOTE TIGHE SON, IF
TAKES IT MAKES IT TO THE END I'M
GOING TO VOTE."
I WISH I WOULD HAVEN'T PLAYED
THE IDOL THEN I WOULD HAVE IT
FOR NEXT TIME.
ALTHOUGH I TRUST MY ALLIANCE
ENOUGH THAT THAT SHOULDN'T BE OF
MUCH CONCERN.
>> LET'S DECIDE WHO WE'RE VOTING
FOR RIGHT NOW NEXT TIME.
>> DIDN'T WE ALREADY SAY?
>> HAYDEN?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: OKAY, HAYDEN IT IS.
IF HE WINS THE CHALLENGE IT'S
KATIE.
WE CAN REMIND EACH OTHER ABOUT
IT.
HE'S COMING BACK.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL:
TINA, LAURA, AND CALEB VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CALEB, I DON'T THINK YOU EVEN
LOOKED UP AT THIS TRIBE OF
PEOPLE THAT VOTED YOU OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL.
>> YOU'D BE CORRECT.
>> Jeff: NOTHING TO SAY TO
THEM?
>> UM, THERE'S TWO FACES I'D
HAVE SOME GOOD WORDS FOR.
BUT JUST AFRAID TO LOOK THE
WRONG PLACE.
>> Jeff: WHO ARE THE TWO?
>> KATIE AND HAYDEN.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY ELSE IS --
>> A MAN'S WORD IS A MAN'S WORD
AND IN THE SOUTH IT MEANS
SOMETHING AND IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" AND UTAH AND PHILLY
IT DOESN'T MEAN AS MUCH.
>> Jeff: TYSON AND GERVASE, I
THINK HE'S POINTING YOU TWO OUT.
UTAH AND PHILLY.
ANY THOUGHT'S ON THAT?
A MAN'S WORD IS A MAN'S WORD
EXCEPT IN PHILLY, GERVASE?
>> IT'S TRUE.
I'M OLD SCHOOL, YOUR WORD IS
YOUR BOND AND WE MADE A BOND
WITH CALEB AND HAYDEN AND FROM
WHAT I HEARD THEY TRIED TO DO US
DIRTY FIRST SO WE GOT SMART AND
DID IT TO THEM BEFORE THEY GOT
US AND I THINK THAT'S SORE LOSER
STATUS RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET TO TODAY'S
DUEL.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL WE'LL HAVE 150
WOODEN TILES.
USE THEM TO BUILD A HOUSE OF
CARDS.
THE FIRST TWO TO BUILD A HOUSE
OF CARDS EIGHT FEED TALL OR THE
TWO WITH THE HIGHEST STACK OF
CARDS AFTER 30 MINUTES LIVE TO
SEE ANOTHER SHOT TO GET BACK IN
THIS GAME.
THE LOSER IS OUT OF THIS GAME
FOR GOOD.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER OF THIS
DUAL DECIDES WHO GETS THE CLUE
TO THE LOCATION OF THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
SOMETHING YOU DID WHEN YOU WERE
A KID.
HOUSE OF CARDS.
JUST NOT WITH A MILLION DOLLARS
ATTACHED TO IT.
THE FIRST TWO TO REACH THE TOP
OF THE POST WHICH IS EIGHT FEED
OR IF WE GO 30 MINUTES, THE TWO
OF W THE HIGHEST STACK WILL
SURVIVE OUT HERE.
THERE'S DEFINITELY A LEARNING
CURVE TO THIS.
SO IF YOU DROP, DON'T PANIC,
JUST START AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T LET IT BE DEMORALIZIN
DEMORALIZING.
JUST PICK UP AND CONTINUE ON.
>> GOOD JOB, MAMA.
>> Jeff: LAURA MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS.
A GIGANTIC LEAD OVER CALEB AND
TINA.
AND THIS IS WHERE IT GETS VERY
DELICATE.
>> Jeff: TAKE YOUR TIME, MOM.
ONE JITTERY HAND, ONE MISSTEP,
THAT WHOLE STACK COMES DOWN AND
YOU HAVE TO START OVER AND
SUDDENLY CALEB AND TINA ARE NOW
IN IT.
TINA A LITTLE OVER THREE FEET.
CALEB RIGHT AROUND TWO.
LAURA GETTING CLOSER SHE'S AT
SEVEN AND A HALF FEET.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
THAT'S OKAY.
>> Jeff: SHE LOSES THE TOP
PART BUT MANAGES TO SAVE
EVERYTHING ELSE.
LAURA LOSES ANOTHER CARD.
THIS IS WHY YOU NEVER GIVE UP.
BEING KROES IS NOT BEING
FINISHED.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, MOM.
>> Jeff: LAURA RECOVERS.
SEEMS TO BE OKAY FOR THE MOMENT.
STILL HAS A GOOD TO GO.
AT NEARLY EIGHT FEET SHE HAS TO
BE VERY CAREFUL SHE DOES NOT
DISRUPT THAT STACK.
LAURA VERY, VERY CLOSE.
ONE CARD AWAY.
THIS WILL DO IT.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
LAURA WINS THIS DUEL, STAYS
ALIVE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
ANOTHER GREAT PERFORMANCE AND
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE NOW.
CALEB OR TINA.
>> GREAT JOB, GIRL.
>> YOU GOT A GOOD LEAD ON HIM,
TINA, SO RELAX.
>> Jeff: THERE ARE THREE
MINUTES LEFT IN THIS DUEL.
>> GOOD JOB, MOM.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: THREE MINUTES TO
REACH THE EIGHT-FOOT POINT OR
THREE MINUTES TO BE HIGHER THAN
THE OTHER PERSON.
WHOSE EVER STACK IS THE HIGHEST
WILL MOVE ON.
>> THAT'S OKAY, TINA.
THAT'S OKAY.
>> Jeff: TINA LOSES PART OF
HER STACK.
TINA AND CALEB NOW ARE ABOUT
DEAD EVEN.
CALEB IS MAKING A BIT OF A RUN.
>> HE'S GETTING A BIT OF A LEAD.
>> Jeff: CALEB SENSING THAT
MOMENTUM.
TINA NEEDS TO GET IT BACK.
WE'RE DOWN TO TWO MINUTES LEFT
IN THIS DUEL.
>> TINA, YOU'VE GOT TO PICK IT
UP, TINA.
>> Jeff: TINA STRUGGLING WITH
THE SAME STACK.
>> MOM, MAYBE CLIMB UP.
>> Jeff: CALEB PULLING AWAY
NOW.
CALEB WITH ABOUT TWO AND A HALF
FEET LEFT.
TINA WITH THREE FEET LEFT.
THIS IS GOING TO COME DOWN TO
THE WIRE.
ONE MINUTE LEFT.
>> CAREFUL.
CAREFUL.
>> Jeff: TINA LOSES PART OF
THE BACK HALF OF HER STRUCTURE.
CALEB IS GETTING HIGHER BUT HIS
STACK IS DEFINITELY CROOKED.
A MILLION DOLLARS ON THE LINE.
WE'RE DOWN TO 30 SECONDS.
CALEB'S ENTIRE STACK --
>> JUST STAY THERE.
JUST STAY THERE.
>> Jeff: -- FELL TO THE
GROUND.
TINA HAS A NEW STRATEGY.
TINA IS GOING TO SIT THERE.
SHE KNOWS CALEB CAN'T CATCH HER.
WE'RE DOWN TO TEN SECONDS LEFT.
>> TEN, NINE, EIGHT, SEVEN, SIX
--
>> Jeff: COUNTING IT DOWN.
COUNT IT.
>> FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE!
>> Jeff: TINA SURVIVORS.
WILL LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER DAY ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> GOOD TRY, CALEB.
>> Jeff: JOINS LAURA IN
CONTINUING THEIR QUEST TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
>> I'M SORRY, CALEB.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> OH, MY GOSH, GOOD JOB, HONEY.
>> Jeff: LAURA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
ANOTHER WIN AT REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
TINA, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: YOU BOTH STAY ALIVE.
CALEB, 30 DAYS IN THIS GAME, I'M
GUESSING YOU IMPRESSED A LOT OF
PEOPLE WITH YOUR WORK ETHIC AND
THE WAY YOU HANDLE COLTON.
>> PROBABLY.
>> Jeff: YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WHICH IS STILL A MYSTERY TO ME.
>> THE RELATIONSHIP WILL STAY A
MIST TROY A LOT OF PEOPLE AND,
YOU KNOW, OPPOSITES ATTRACT.
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE SIMILAR,
OPPOSITES ATTRACT.
>>
>> Jeff: IN WHAT WAYS ARE YOU
SIMILAR?
>> WE'RE BOTH GUYS.
HIS ESTROGEN LEVEL IS PROBABLY
HIGHER THAN MINE BUT THAT'S
PROBABLY ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CALEB.
AFTER 30 DAYS YOU ARE OUT OF
THIS GAME.
YOU CAN TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE
URN.
(APPLAUSE)
>> LOVE YOU, CALEB.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAURA,
ONCE AGAIN YOU GET TO DETERMINE
WHO GETS THE CLUE TO THE
LOCATION OF THE IDOL.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO GIVE IT TO?
>> MY GIRL CIERA.
>> Jeff: CIERA ONCE AGAIN GETS
THE CLUE.
>> I'M GOING TO KEEP IT.
>> Jeff: THIS TIME CIERA IS
GOING TO KEEP THE CLUE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: GO FIND THAT.
DIG, GIRL.
FIND THAT IDOL.
>> Jeff: LAURA, TINA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AWAIT YOUR NEXT COMPETITOR AND
YOUR NEXT DUEL.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, GRAB YOUR
STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> WORKING IT.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST REDEMPTION
ISLAND I'VE GONE TO WHERE I'VE
BEEN LIKE, MOM, YOU BETTER PULL
THIS ONE OUT.
WE KNEW TYSON PLAYED AN IDOL
WHICH MEANT THERE WAS GOING TO
BE A NEW ONE PROBABLY IN PLAY.
>> WE NEED WATER.
>> WE'RE OUT OF WATER?
I'LL GET SOME WATER.
>> Jeff: THE BIG QUESTION HAS
BEEN IF MY MOM WINS DO I TAKE
THE CLUE?
AND I KIND OF FELT LIKE I NEEDED
TO BECAUSE IF KATIE GETS IT OR
IF HAYDEN GETS IT, THAT'S BAD
NEWS FOR SOUSE WE'RE GOING TO
OPEN IT AS A GROUP, WE'LL FIND
IT AND DECIDE WHAT TO DO WITH
IT.
>> READY?
LET'S SEE WHAT THIS BAD BOY
SAYS.
"NOT TOO FAR FROM YOUR WATER,
NOT TOO CLOSE TO THE GROUND
HIDES INCREDIBLE POWER BUT ONLY
IF IT'S FOUND."
"NOT TOO FAR FROM YOUR WATER.
NOT TOO CLOSE TO THE GROUND."
>> IN A TREE.
>> CIERA OPENS UP THE CLUE AND
READS IT ALOUD AND I WAS LIKE,
YES!
>> SHOULD WE START LOOKING?
>> YEAH.
>> I SAY WE SPY ON THEM.
>> YEAH, WE CAN DO THAT.
>> SO NOW EVERYBODY SCATTERS AND
LOOKING AND LOOKING AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN HAYDEN WALKS UP.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS LOOKING
FOR?
>> NOTHING.
>> I CRUISE TOWARDS THE WELL AND
TYSON, GERVASE, CIERA AND MONICA
ARE ALL DOWN THERE PEEKING
AROUND LOOKING IN TREES LIKE
HUNTING, SEARCHING AND IT'S
OBVIOUS.
THE IDOL IS DOWN THERE
SOMEWHERE.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO STICK BACK
HERE AND LOOK?
>> I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR A
MINUTE.
IT'S MY LAST HOPE.
I HAVE TO LOOK AND FIND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> THIS IS STUPID.
>> I USED THE IDOL AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND A NEW ONE
CAME BACK INTO PLAY AND I HAVE
TO FIND IT OTHERWISE I DON'T
KNOW WHO'S GOING TO HAVE IT.
SO SO THE SAFEST THING FOR ME TO
DO IS TO FIND THE IDOL.
I'M THREAT NUMBER ONE AND
EVERYONE KNOWS THAT AND I KNOW
THAT.
I'M JUST TRYING TO PLAY THE GAME
AND TRYING TO GET TO THE END AND
I TOLD MYSELF WHEN RACHEL LEFT
THAT IF I WAS GOING TO STAY I
HAD TO GET TO THE END.
SO THAT -- IT'S THE ONLY WAY
THAT IT WOULD BE WORTH IT FOR ME
TO STAY HERE AND NOT GO IN WHEN
I COULD HAVE SAVED HER.
SO I'VE JUST BEEN FIGHTING AND
CLAWING AND I'M SO CLOSE.
AND I STILL FEEL LIKE IT'S GOING
TO GET PULLED OUT FROM UNDER ME.
AND I HATE THAT FEELING BECAUSE
I'VE WORKED TOO HARD TO GET
HERE.
BOOM!
I DON'T HAVE POCKETS ON ANY OF
MY CLOTHES SO I'VE GOT TO PUT IT
RIGHT IN MY CRASH WHERE NOBODY
WILL SUSPECT A BULGE.
NOW THE TRICK IS, DO I SHARE IT
WITH EVERYBODY OR KEEP IT TO
MYSELF AGAIN?
I THINK I'LL KEEP IT TO MYSELF.
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
I CAN REST EASY.
I HAVE THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT'S UP TO ME TO JUST STAY
FOCUSED AND DON'T LET HAYDEN WIN
THE CHALLENGE.
THAT'S THE NUMBER ONE THING,
HAYDEN CAN'T WIN.
THAT WAS THE DICIEST MOMENT OF
THE GAME FOR ME SO FAR WAS
HAVING THAT IDOL ON THE LOOSE SO
-- NOW I CAN PROBABLY TAKE A NAP
TODAY.
I WAS NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
TAKE A NAP UNLESS I FOUND THAT
THING.
OKAY.
DID IT AGAIN.
NAP TIME.
>> WHERE'S YOUR HEAD AT, BRO?
WHERE'S YOUR HEAD AT?
>> IN THE GAME, AS ALWAYS.
>> LAST NIGHT WHEN YOU TOLD ME
YOU WERE OKAY WITH SECOND PLACE,
I KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> I'M GLAD YOU DO.
>> I STRUCK A NERVE WITH GERVASE
SO I THINK GERVASE IS OPEN TO
WORKING WITH ME.
BLIND SIDING TYSON.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO DO IT.
>> FROM MY PERSPECTIVE, I DON'T
SEE A MOVE.
TELL ME A MOVE TO MAKE.
>> IF I HAVE KATIE-- WHICH I
DO-- AND I GET CIERA, YOU'RE ON?
>> YOU HAVE TO GET CIERA.
IT'S GOT TO BE -- YOU HAVE TO
LOOK AT MY FACE AND TELL ME
GERJ, IT'S 100%.
I THINK TYSON IS PLAYING THE
GAME WELL BUT I'M NOT PUTTING MY
TRUST AND FAITH IN HAYDEN AT
ALL.
I HAVE MY TRUST AND FAITH IN
TYSON AND IT'S GOT ME THIS FIRST
BUT I WANT THOSE OPTIONS OUT
THERE AND HAYDEN'S A GOOD OPTION
TO HAVE.
>> I WON'T DO ANYTHING TO BLOW
UP YOUR GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR THE THIRD TIME,
I'LL TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE FROM
MONICA.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES WHILE BALANCING A
BALL ON TOP OF A POLE.
AT THE END OF EACH OBSTACLE,
YOU'LL ADD ANOTHER SECTION OF
POLE MAKING IT MORE DIFFICULT TO
BALANCE.
THE BALL DROPS, YOU GO BACK.
ONCE YOU REACH THE END YOU'LL
RELEASE A KEY, UNLOCK A BOX AND
USE THE SANDBAGS INSIDE THE TO
KNOCK OVER NINE BAMBOO TARGETS.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER IS
PLAYING FOR REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF THIS
CHALLENGE WILL ENJOY AN
AFTERNOON OF ICE CREAM.
YOU'LL HAVE A "SURVIVOR" ICE
CREAM CART DELIVERED TO YOUR
CAMP.
ICE CREAM BARS, ICE CREAM
SANDWICHES, ICE CREAM CONES.
SO WHILE EVERYBODY ELSE IS
WORRIED ABOUT THE VOTE, YOU WILL
HAVE THE CERTAINTY OF IMMUNITY
AND A BELLYFUL OF ICE CREAM.
BIG STAKES.
EVERYTHING MATTERS AT THIS
POINT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST SECTION IS EASY, JUST ONE
BIT OF POLL.
TYSON DROPS QUICKLY, HAS TO GO
BACK.
EVERYBODY ELSE DOING A NICE JOB.
YOU WANT TO TAKE YOUR TIME.
HAYDEN HAS TO GO BACK.
THAT FIRST POLE YOU HAVE TO GO
UNDER, THE BALL HAS TO GO OVER.
CIERA'S GOT TO COME BACK!
KAY DEN'S GOT TO COME BACK.
MONICA IS THROUGH.
MONICA ONCE AGAIN OFF TO A FAST
START IN AN INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
GERVASE IS THROUGH.
TYSON IS THROUGH.
MONICA, TYSON, GERVASE WORKING
ON THEIR POLES, HAYDEN IS NOW
THROUGH.
CIERA AND KATIE BRINGING UP THE
REAR.
MONICA STARTING ON HER SECOND
SECTION.
TYSON ALREADY DROPPING.
KATIE'S GOOD.
CIERA'S GOOD.
MONICA OUT TO AN EARLY LEAD.
GERVASE RIGHT BEHIND.
HERE COMES HAYDEN AND TYSON.
HAYDEN'S GOT TO GO BACK.
THIS REQUIRES PATIENCE, BALANCE,
HAYDEN TRYING TO GET IN THIS.
KATIE CAN'T EVEN GET ON THE
BEAM.
MONICA'S THROUGH THE SECOND
SECTION.
GERVASE IS THROUGH THE SECOND
TYSON IS THROUGH THE SECOND
SECTION.
MONICA ALREADY HAS HER THIRD
SECTION OF POLE.
THIS IS AS TOUGH AS THIS
CHALLENGE WILL GET RIGHT HERE.
HAYDEN'S THROUGH THE SECOND
SECTION.
IT IS HAYDEN, TYSON, GERVASE AND
MONICA.
OH, KATIE JUST TOOK IT ON THE
HEAD!
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
KATIE FALLING OUT OF THIS.
CIERA VERY SLOW FALLING OUT OF
IT.
TYSON DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO COME BACK.
IT IS MONICA STILL IN THE LEAD.
SHE'S WON THREE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITIES.
GERVASE RIGHT BEHIND HER.
BOTH HAVE BEEN PERFECT IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
MONICA IS THROUGH.
GERVASE IS THROUGH.
IT IS MONICA AND GERVASE.
HAYDEN DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
TYSON WOULD LOVE TO CATCH UP BUT
HE'S GOT TO HUSTLE.
MONICA'S AT HER KEY STATION.
GERVASE NOW AT HIS KEY STATION.
JERVAS AND MONICA BOTH RELEASE
THEIR KEYS.
MONICA HAS HER SANDBAGS AND
SHE'S STARTING TO THROW.
SHE HAS BEEN ON A TEAR IN THIS
SEASON.
GERVASE KNOCKS DOWN THREE RIGHT
AWAY.
MONICA KNOCKS DOWN HER SECOND.
TYSON IS THROUGH.
>> OH, GOD.
>> Jeff:ER HAVE SKWRAS KNOCKS
DOWN THREE MORE.
EGERVASE QUICKLY DOWN TO TWO
LEFT.
HE'S PLOWING THROUGH THIS.
GERVASE DOWN TO ONE LEFT.
VERY CLOSE!
MONICA DOWN TO FIVE LEFT.
MAKE IT FOUR.
GERVASE HAS WON!
MONICA KNOCKS DOWN ANOTHER!
TYSON IN IT NOW.
HE KNOCKS DOWN TWO.
GERVASE STILL MISSING THAT LAST
ONE.
MONICA'S DOWN TO THREE.
MONICA HAS TWO LEFT!
TYSON TRYING TO CATCH UP.
ESKWRER GERVASE HAS ONE LEFT.
IT'S MONICA AND GERVASE!
GERVASE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
AND REWARD!
GERVASE, COME ON OVER.
(APPLAUSE)
GERVASE, SAFE FROM THE VOTE
TONIGHT, YOU ARE NOT GOING HOME
ON DAY 32.
IN ADDITION, YOU HAVE A NICE
REWARD COMING TO CAMP.
A "SURVIVOR" ICE CREAM CART.
WHAT COULD BE BETTER ON A A 115
DEGREE DAY?
>> NOTHING BUT ICE CREAM,
CARAMEL SAUCE AND MORE ICE
CREAM.
>> Jeff: ICE CREAM ALONE IS
FINE BUT WITH SOMEBODY ELSE IT'S
MORE FUN.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON WHO WILL JOIN
YOU AT CAMP TO FEAST ON THE ICE
CREAM.
>> I'LL TAKE MONICA.
>> Jeff: MONICA, COME ON OVER,
JOIN GERVASE.
>> THANKS, JERV, MEANS A LOT.
>> Jeff: IS THIS PAYBACK FOR
THE DAY SHE GAVE UP THAT BURGERS
AND HOT DOGS?
>> NOW THE BURDEN IS OFF MY
SHOULDERS.
>> Jeff: TWO IS FUN, THREE'S A
PARTY.
ONE MORE PERSON.
>> OH, YOU'RE KILLING ME!
>> Jeff: PEOPLE HAVE MADE
MILLION DOLLAR MISTAKES AT THIS
POINT IN THE GAME.
WHO DO YOU CHOOSE AND WHO DO YOU
LEAVE BEHIND?
>> I'VE GOT TO GO WITH MY LEFT
HAND MAN TYSON.
>> Jeff: TYSON, COME ON OVER.
HOW'S THAT FEEL, TYSON?
>> GOOD.
I'M LEFT HANDED SO I'M ASSUMING
THAT'S WHY HE SAID LEFT HAND
MAN.
>> (LAUGHS).
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT, SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
YOU WILL HAVE TO FIGHT TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANKS.
>> WITH THE BIG ARM.
>> THANKS, EVERYONE.
SO FINALLY, 32 DAYS INTO THE
GAME I WIN IMMUNITY.
>> AWESOME.
>> DID YOU TAKE GYMNASTICS WHEN
YOU WERE A KID, DUDE?
>> I KIND OF DID.
>> YOU ROCKED THAT BALANCE BEAM.
>> I'M IN A GREAT POSITION NO
MATTER WHICH WAY I PLAYTHINGS.
I'M IN A SECURE ALLIANCE.
ME, TYSON, MONICA, THE THREE,
TOGETHER.
WE HAVE CIERA WHICH MAKES FOUR.
WE PRETTY MUCH CONTROL THE GAME.
>> DO YOU HEAR THAT?
>> ICE CREAM!
ICE CREAM!
>> ROOT BEER FLOAT, YEAH, I WANT
THAT.
>> ME, TOO.
>> IS THAT A BEER?
>> ROOT BEER.
>> DO THEY HAVE TO DO IT RIGHT
IN FRONT OF CAMP?
>> GERVASE DECIDED TO CHOOSE
MONICA AND TYSON TO EAT ICE
CREAM WITH THEM AND THAT LEAVES
THE DOOR OPEN FOR ME TO TALK TO
CIERA AND PITCH HER THE IDEA,
HEY, CIERA, LET'S MAKE A MOVE
HERE.
>> SO SAY KATIE GOES HOME
TONIGHT OR I GO HOME TONIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: WHO DO YOU HONESTLY
THINK IS GOING TO GO HOME NEXT
WEEK?
DO YOU THINK KATIE GOES HOME
NEXT WEEK?
DO YOU THINK I GO HOME?
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE YOU.
>> I THINK IT'S YOU.
>> Jeff: WELL, I MEAN, I WOULD
LIKE -- I WOULD HOPE IT WOULD BE
ONE OF YOU TWO.
PART OF MY STRATEGY HAS BEEN
MAKING HAYDEN AND KATIE FEEL
LIKE THEY HAVE, LIKE, A GLIMMER
OF HOPE.
BUT I HAVE NO INTENTION OF DOING
ANYTHING WITH HAYDEN AND KATIE.
>> Jeff: YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S WHAT WILL HAPPEN?
>> YES.
AND THAT'S MY HONEST OPINION.
WHAT ARE YOU WANTING TO HAVE
HAPPEN?
>> I MEAN, I'M IN A TOUGH SPOT
BECAUSE IT'S GOING TO BE ME MOST
LIKELY.
>> OKAY.
>> I GET THAT.
>> BUT IF WE HAD THE MAJORITY
WOULD YOU MAKE A BIG MOVE?
>> DEPENDS ON WHO YOUR MAJORITY
IS.
>> GERVASE IS ON BOARD IF YOU'RE
ON BOARD.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU WANTING TO DO
AT THIS POINT RIGHT NOW?
>> HERE'S THE THING.
TYSON MAY OR MAY NOT HAVE AN
IDOL.
YOU CAN EITHER MAKE A STINK AT
TRIBAL LIKE WE'RE GOING TO VOTE
OUT TYSON AND MAKE HIM FLUSH HIS
IDOL AND VOTE OUT MONICA OR WE
CAN TRY AND BE SLY.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A RESUME TO WIN
AND YOU HAVE TO HAVE SAID YOU
MADE A BIG MOVE AND THIS COULD
BE THAT FOR YOU.
>> AND ALL I'M TELLING YOU IS --
I MEAN, WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE
VOTES RIGHT NOW, FOR ME TO VOTE
WITH YOU GUYS TWAOUB 3-3 VOTE
AND I'M NOT DOING THAT.
>> Jeff: GERVASE AND CIERA
RIGHT NOW CAN MAKE A HUGE MOVE
AND GET OUT TYSON.
IF THEY MAKE THIS MOVE THEY
PROBABLY DESERVE TO WIN THIS
GAME.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS, I WANT TO
TALK TO YOU BOTH.
YOU DON'T WANT SECOND PLACE.
IF WE ALL VOTE TOGETHER WE HAVE
FOUR.
THE THREE OF US, KATIE, TYSON
WILL NEVER SEE IT COMING.
TYSON GOES HOME.
NEXT WEEK KATIE GOES HOME.
IT'S A HUGE MOVE.
IF YOU WANT TO GET HIM OUT, IT'S
THIS TRIBAL RIGHT NOW.
HE'S NOT EXPECTING IT.
>> HE HAS THE NUMBERS.
>> HE HAS THE NUMBERS BUT HE
KNOWS THAT NOBODY -- HE KNOWS
EVERYBODY THINKS THAT THEY'RE
GOING TO LOSE HIM-TO-HIM IN THE
END-- WHICH THEY ARE.
>> I THINK I HAVE A CHANCE TO
BEAT TYSON BECAUSE TYSON HAS
DONE THE SAME CRIMES.
>> HE HAS, BUT HE'S PLAYED THE
GAME.
>> TONIGHT IS SIMPLE: HAYDEN'S
GOT TO GO AND THEN THANK
GOODNESS IT CAN BE KATIE NEXT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE'S STILL
AROUND.
>> I AGREE WITH GERV.
KATIE HAS JUST A BIG A SHOT OF
ME AT THE END AND YOU, DO, TOO.
>> YOU WANT TO WIN FIRST PLACE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO TO THE END
AND GET SECOND OR THIRD?
SECOND PLACE IS THE FIRST LOSER.
>> WHAT I WAS HOPING WAS CIERA
AND GERVASE WERE GOING TO ROLL
WITH ME TO BLIND SIDE TYSON AND
THEY'RE NOT DOING IT.
I DON'T LIKE TO LOSE.
I'M THE WORST -- THE WORST
LOSER.
GOT!
TYSON, I'M SITTING HERE TRYING
TO CONVINCE EVERYONE TO BLIND
SIDE YOU.
IT'S NOT -- IT HASN'T WORKED.
>> GOOD.
>> YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU, BUT I'M
JUST TRYING TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW YOU ARE.
>> YUP.
>> THAT'S THE WAY IT GOES.
>> TONIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO INTO
TRIBAL GUNS BLAZING.
I'M GOING TO GO IT N AND BLOW IT
UP.
LET THINGS FLY.
GO DOWN SWINGING.
MAYBE IT WON'T BE ME.
WE'LL SEE.
WE WILL SEE.
THE CHAPTER IS NOT CLOSED YET.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ARAS, VYTAS, AND CALEB.
OKAY, SO AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL THERE WAS A VERY CLEAR
DIVISION OF GERVASE, MONICA,
TYSON, AND CIERA AND THEN IT WAS
HAYDEN, KATIE AND CALEB WHO WAS
VOTED OUT.
SO, HAYDEN, IS IT SAFE TO ASSUME
IT'S STILL THAT DIVISION ONLY
NOW IT'S 4-2?
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
THE FOUR OF THEM ARE BEING
CONTROLLED BY TYSON.
THE TWO OF US ARE ON OUR OWN.
>> Jeff: BOY, THOSE ARE BIG
WORDS, CIERA.
HE JUST SAID YOU WERE BEING
CONTROLLED BY TYSON.
>> YEAH.
LET HIM THINK WHAT HE WANTS TO
THINK.
I'M COMFORTABLE IN MY POSITION
WITH MY ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: ALTHOUGH YOU WEREN'T
CHOSEN TODAY BY GERVASE AS PART
OF THE REWARD.
>> I THINK HIS DECISION WAS
BASED ON THE FACT THAT I HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO BE A PART OF A LOT
OF THE FOOD REWARDS SO I DIDN'T
TAKE ANY OFFENSE TO IT.
>> IT'S OBVIOUS THE TWO PEOPLE
ARE CHOSE ARE ORIGINAL TKPWA
LANG MEMBERS.
I PUT MY BLOOD SWEAT AND TEARS
IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: CIERA, THAT SPEECH
RIGHT THERE IS GREAT IF YOU'RE
TYSON AND MONICA.
NOT SO GOOD IF YOU'RE CIERA.
>> I AGREE 100%.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, THIS IS THE
OPPORTUNITY YOU NEED BECAUSE YOU
AND KATIE HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE.
IF YOU CAN SWAY CIERA TO GO 3-3,
NOW WE HAVE A NEW GAME.
>> JEFF, THAT'S IT.
AND, AGAIN, TYSON'S CONTROLLING
THESE PEOPLE.
CALEB AND I TOOK A BACKSEAT
WHILE TYSON POINTED FINGERS AND
SAID OKAY, IT'S ARAS.
OR IT'S VYTAS.
OR, HEY, IT'S LAURA.
>> WAS I THE ONE THAT VOTED YOUR
MOM SNOUT.
>> NO.
AND ACTUALLY HAYDEN AND CALEB
WERWERE THE ONES WHO SAID THEY
WANTED TO VOTE MY MOM OUT.
>> Jeff: KATIE, WHERE DO YOU
FIT IN IN ALL THIS?
>> WELL, DURING THIS WHOLE
POLITICAL WHAT HAVE YOU --
>> Jeff: HOLD ON.
HOLD ON.
WHEN YOU SAY DURING THAT WHOLE
POLITICAL WHATEVER, THAT IS
"SURVIVOR."
THIS IS WHERE THE GAME IS WON OR
LOST.
DO YOU GET THAT?
>> WELL, I'VE BEEN AT THE BOTTOM
SO I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO BE A
PART OF THESE CONVERSATIONS.
>> Jeff: MONICA, WHY WOULD IT
MAKE SENSE FOR CIERA TO SAY THAT
TYSON MONICA GERVASE TRIO ARE
TIGHT, MAYBE I NEED GO WITH
HAYDEN AND KATIE AND HAVE A SHOT
TO THE END?
>> THAT'S A BAD MOVE.
BECAUSE FOUR IS BETTER THAN SIX.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT TYPE OF
PROMISES HAVE BEEN MADE TO
PEOPLE BECAUSE PEOPLE AT THIS
POINT START TO THINK ABOUT WHO
CAN I BEAT?
>> CAN I SAY SOMETHING, JEFF?
MONICA JUST SAID TO CIERA 4 IS
BETTER THAN 6 WHICH IMMEDIATELY
MEANS CIERA, YOU'RE NUMBER FOUR.
IF YOU CAME ON THIS SIDE, THERE
IS NO FOUR FIVE OR SIX.
THERE'S ONE, TWO AND THREE.
OR ONE, TWO, AND THREE.
HOWEVER YOU FRAME IT.
>> THAT'S INCORRECT.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN THAT'S
INCORRECT?
>> WHAT SHE HAS ON THAT SIDE IS
A BACK STABBER, A BACK STABBER,
A LIAR, A LIAR.
WHAT SHE HAS ON THIS SIDE IS
HONEST WORDS, PEOPLE WHO KEEP
THEIR WORD AND KEEP IT TOGETHER.
>>
(LAUGHTER)
>> WHY IS THE JURY LAUGHING?
>> BECAUSE THEY TRIED TO STAB US
IN THE BACK AND GOT PLAYED
FIRST!
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE LAUGHING.
NOBODY'S ENTERTAINING ANY IDEAS
OF JUMPING SHIP IN THIS
ALLIANCE.
IT'S ONE TWO THREE AND FOUR.
AND HAYDEN, GUESS THAT?
YOU'RE GOING ON A JURY!
BELIEVE THAT!
YOU'RE GOING TO BE ON THE JURY.
>> I'M SURE.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
BUT GERVASE, ONCE AGAIN, CIERA
WAS NUMBER FOUR WHEN YOU COUNTED
IT OUT.
>> JUST HOW I'M COUNTING.
CIERA KNOWS ONE THING FOR
CERTAIN: SHE'S NOT GOING HOME
TONIGHT SO SHE CAN RUN WITH THAT
TO THE BANK.
BUT IF SHE WANTS TO GO HOME, THE
TIME TO MAKE A MOVE IS NOW.
>> Jeff: TYSON, THAT'S NOT
NECESSARILY TRUE.
YOU CAN DIVIDE THIS 3-3, SPLIT
IT UP AND FORCE PEOPLE TO DRAW
ROCKS.
>> I DON'T THINK CIERA'S FOUR.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> WELL, THEN THAT WOULD MEAN
MONICA WOULD BE FOUR.
>> PERHAPS.
>> THERE'S NO PERHAPS ABOUT IT.
IF CIERA'S NOT FOUR YOU ARE
FOUR.
>> YOU'RE ASSUMING ME AND
GERVASE ARE ONE AND TWO?
>> YES, I AM.
>> CIERA, I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT
NOW, I'VE NEVER BETRAYED YOU.
THESE GUYS HAVE BOTH WRITTEN
YOUR NAME DOWN AND I'VE
PROTECTED YOU AND KEPT YOU WITH
US AND I'M PLANNING ON STAYING
WITH THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: CIERA, BUCKNUMER BE
FOUR ALL DAY LONG.
YOU CAN COME WITH US, WE CAN
DRAW ROCKS.
>> CIERA --
>> AND THAT'S A BIG MOVE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: CIERA, WHAT DID HE
SAY WHEN HE CAME BACK TO CAMP
AFTER CALEB WENT HOME?
WHO'S GETTING HIS VOTE, TYSON?
>> BUT THAT WAS TO RUFFLE YOUR
FEATHERS GERVASE?
>> DO YOU WANT SOMEBODY
WISHY-WASHY OR PEOPLE WHO HAVE
BEEN 100 WITH YOU?
WE'VE BEEN 100.
>> AIR IS IT WAS TO RILE
FEATHERS.
>> RUFFLE.
RUFFLE FEATHERS.
YOU SAID RUSTLE FEATHERS.
>> RUSTLE, RUFFLE, WHATEVER.
>> RUSTLE IS A FIRST NAME.
>> R-U-S-TLE.
RUSTLING LEAVES.
>> Jeff: THAT'S THE CRAZIEST
CONVERSATION I'VE EVER HEARD
BEFORE A POTENTIALLY MILLION
DOLLAR VOTE.
>> CIERA, 1-4 OVER THERE AND YOU
KNOW YOU'RE NUMBER FOUR.
YOU MAKE A BIG MOVE AND IT WORKS
OUT YOU'RE A MILLIONAIRE AT THE
END OF THE GAME.
>> AND IF IT DOESN'T WORK OUT
YOU CAN BE GOING HOME TONIGHT BY
DRAWING A ROCK.
>> Jeff: WOW.
IT'S BEEN A CRAZY TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
LET'S SEE WHERE IT ALL COMES
OUT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KATIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> DON'T HATE THE PLAYERS,
HOMEY, HATE THE GAME!
THIS ISN'T PWROEZ, IT'S
"SURVIVOR."
WE DO THINGS DIFFERENT HERE.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET A LESSON IN
HOW TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> NEVER TELL AN INSANE PERSON
THEY'RE GOING HOME NEXT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT NOW
WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LI THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE FIRST.
FIRST VOTE, HAYDEN.
HAYDEN.
MONICA.
THAT'S TWO VOTES MONICA; TWO
VOTES HAYDEN.
HAYDEN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES HAYDEN, TWO
VOTES MONICA, ONE VOTE LEFT.
MONICA.
WE'RE TIED.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN.
WE'LL REVOTE.
KPHAOPB WON'T VOTE.
HAYDEN WILL NOT VOTE.
YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR HAYDEN OR
MONICA.
KATIE, YOU'LL COME GET THIS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
MONICA.
HAYDEN.
THAT'S TWO VOTES MONICA, ONE
VOTE HAYDEN, ONE VOTE LEFT.
WE ARE DEADLOCKED.
PER THE RULES OF "SURVIVOR,"
KATIE, CIERA, TYSON, AND
GERVASE, IF THE FOUR OF YOU CAN
UNANIMOUSLY COME UP WITH ONE
NAME-- EITHER HAYDEN OR MONICA
TO KICK OUT OF THIS GAME--
THEY'RE OUT.
OTHERWISE HAYDEN BECOMES SAFE,
MONICA BECOMES SAFE, GERVASE IS
SAFE BECAUSE HE HAS IMMUNITY,
KATIE, CIERA, AND TYSON WILL
DRAW ROCKS.
>> OKAY, YOU GUYS, THIS IS WHERE
I'M AT RIGHT HERE.
I'M NUMBER FOUR SO LET'S NOT
BULL (BLEEP) ME.
I AM NUMBER FOUR.
>> HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
>> THEN COOL.
THEN WE'LL DRAW A ROCK.
>> FINE, LET'S DRAW ROCKS.
>> DRAW ROCKS?
>> I'LL DRAW ROCKS UNLESS
SOMEBODY'S VOTING MY WAY I'M
DRAWING ROCKS.
>> I'LL DRAW ROCKS, TOO.
>> OKAY, WE'RE DRAWING ROCKS.
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN.
KATIE, CIERA, TYSON WILL DRAW
ROCKS.
THERE ARE TWO BLACK ROCKS IN
HERE.
THERE IS ONE WHITE ROCK.
BLACK MEANS YOU ARE SAFE, WHITE
IS THE SAME AS BEING VOTED OUT.
YOU'LL LEAVE THIS TRIBE AND HEAD
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
ARE WE CLEAR?
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE ONE, PLEASE DON'T LOOK AT
IT.
ALL RIGHT.
WHITE MEANS YOU ARE GOING HOME,
BLACK MEANS YOU ARE SAFE.
EVERYBODY PUT OUT YOUR PALM.
AND REVEAL.
KATIE HAS DRAWN THE WHITE ROCK.
YOU'RE THE 13th PERSON OUT
OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD OVER.
>> GOOD LUCK.
IT WAS WORTH A TRY.
>> STAY WITH US.
>> KATIE, WANT A HUG?
DANGEROUS MOVE?
BALANCEY, DIDN'T THINK YOU HAD
THE BALANCE TO DO THAT.
THAT'S YOUR CHAIR OVER THERE,
ONE OF THOSE.
>> KATIE, I'M SORRY.
>>'S OKAY.
GET THEM.
>> DON'T GLARE AT ME.
>> I'M NOT GLARING AT YOU.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
>> Jeff: KATIE, YOU MADE A BIG
MOVE, DIDN'T WORK OUT.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> BYE, KATIE.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: THERE ARE NO WORDS
THAT CAN TOP WHAT JUST HAPPENED.
IT'S ONLY THE SECOND TIME IN 27
SEASONS WE'VE DRAWN ROCKS.
THIS GAME IS DEFINITELY ON AND
IT'S CLEAR IT IS GOING TO BE A
BATTLE UNTIL THE VERY END.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> THE LINE'S IN THE SAND.
>> HEY, HAYDEN --
>> I NEED THAT DON'T ANY.
>> IF YOU WANT IT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR" --
>> I WOULD NOT BE OPPOSED TO
LETTING YOU WIN.
>> Jeff: TINA FACES HER
BIGGEST CHALLENGE YET.
ARE YOU CAPABLE OF GIVING 100%?
>> THAT'S A HARD ONE.
>> Jeff: WHILE MONICA GETS
NEWS THAT COULD CHANGE
EVERYTHING.
>> TYSON WAS TALKING MAD CRAP
ABOUT YOU.
>> IF I AM THEIR PUPPY DOG IT'S
NOW BECOME A ME GAME.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> WE HAD TO DRAW ROCKS TONIGHT.
>> UH-UH!
>> YEAH.
>> AND YOU DREW THE ROCK?
>> OH!
>> IT WAS JUST BETWEEN THREE OF
US, THOUGH.
>> WHO DREW FIRST?
>> I DREW FIRST AND I WAS THE
WHITE ROCK.
TONIGHT WAS MY SHOT TO KNOCK
TYSON OFF HIS THRONE BUT I HAD
THE WHITE ROCK SO I WAS ROCKED
OUT.