>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> RETURNING PLAYERS OVER HERE,
NEW PLAYERS OVER THERE.
>> Jeff: IN BLOOD VERSUS
WATER, RETURNING PLAYERS WERE
FORCED TO COMPETE AGAINST THEIR
LOVED ONES, AND AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND ARENA, IT WAS CLEAR THE
GAME WAS TAKING ITS TOLL ON
EVERYONE.
>> WE HAVEN'T WANTED TO VOTE
ANYBODY OUT, BUT WE'VE HAD.
TO.
>> BRAD, THE LEADER OF TADHANA,
TOOK MOST OF THE BLAME.
>> BRAD.
>> WHILE COLTON TOOK THE EASY
WAY OUT.
>> I CAN'T DO THIS.
>> MEANING YOU'RE QUITTING
AGAIN?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
OUT, THE BOAT WILL PICK YOU UP.
QUITTING ON THE GAME AND HIS
TRIBE MATES FOR THE SECOND TIME.
WHEN CANDICE WON HER SECOND DUAL
IN A ROW, SHE GAVE ANOTHER CLUE
TO HER HUSBAND JOHN, AND HE
SHARED IT WITH HIS CLOSEST ALLY,
BRAD.
>> IN THE WATER.
>> Jeff: MEANWHILE, AT GALANG,
A MAJORITY ALLIANCE WAS FORMING.
>> THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE, THIS
IS THE FIVE TO BE IN.
>> IT IS TYSON, ARAS, GERVASE,
TINA AND ME.
EVERYBODY IN THIS ALLIANCE HAS
HAD A LOT OF LIFE EXPERIENCE.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE --
>> TYSON IS IN QUICKLY -- TYSON
INJURED HIS SHOULDER, BUT IT
DIDN'T STOP GALANG FROM WINNING
IMMUNITY FOR THE THIRD TIME IN A
ROW.
GALANG WINS!
FACING ANOTHER TRIBAL COUNCIL,
TALD TAD'S PLAY WAS TO TAKE OUT
THE WEAK.
>> CIERA HASN'T DONE ANYTHING IN
ANY CHALLENGE.
I DON'T THINK SHE'S HELPING US
THAT MUCH.
>> WE CAN'T AFFORD TO HAVE JOHN
AND CANDICE BACK IN THE GAME.
HE NEEDS TO GO.
>> IT'S BEEN FIVE GUYS SINCE DAY
ONE.
IF WE VOTE ONE OUT NOW, IT COULD
BE LIKE OPENING PANDORA'S BOX.
>>
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
TADHANA SIDE WITH JOHN.
JOHN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SENDING JOHN TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND TO BATTLE HIS WIFE.
14 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> CANDICE, IT'S ME.
YEAH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> I'M COMPLETELY SHOCKED.
NO CLUE THAT WAS COMING TONIGHT.
BRAD TOLD ME WE WERE CLOSE.
I SORT OF BELIEVED HIM, SORT OF
DIDN'T, YOU KNOW, BUT HE
REASSURED ME ENOUGH THAT I FELT
COMFORTABLE IT WASN'T GOING TO
BE ME TONIGHT.
>> I KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO BE
TOO TRUSTING OF PEOPLE.
>> NOW WE'RE OUT HERE.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> THAT'S NOT GOOD!
>> I'M DISAPPOINTED.
I WISH I COULD HAVE BEEN THERE
TO GIVE HIM MORE POINTERS AND TO
KEEP HIM ON HIS TOES, BUT HE'S
SO TRUSTING.
AND I LOVE THAT ABOUT HIM, BUT
IT DOESN'T HELP YOU WIN
"SURVIVOR."
>> I LOVE YOU.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN HERE WITHOUT
ME?
>> I WANTED TO BE HERE WITHOUT
YOU THE WHOLE TIME.
>> GOOD WORK, GUYS.
THAT WAS A DOOZY.
>> NOT EASY.
>> EPIC BLINDSIDE.
>> HE WAS GETTING NERVOUS
TOWARDS THE END.
>> YEAH, HE WAS.
>> HE'S NOT A GOOD LIAR.
BUT I HOOKED HIM IN FROM DAY
ONE.
I WAS LIKE, JOHN, YOU'RE MY GUY.
YOU KNOW, HE'S MILITARY.
WHEN WE BLINDSIDED JOHN TONIGHT,
I SPEARHEADED THE THINKING OF
THE FUTURE.
IF THIS WERE SURVIVOR 26 OR
SURVIVOR 25, WE WOULD HAVE
STAYED FIVE GUYS ALL THE WAY
THROUGH.
THIS IS LOVED ONES.
JOHN HAD NO CONNECTION ON THE
OTHER SIDE.
WE NEED TO THINK ABOUT
CONNECTIONS.
OUR LOVED ONES NEED TO
UNDERSTAND, IF WE'RE NOT GOING
TO WIN ON THEIR OWN, THEY NEED
TO TRIP.
THEY NEED TO UNDERSTAND THE
STRATEGY OF THIS "SURVIVOR."
THIS IS NOT US AGAINST THEM,
THIS IS SOME AGAINST OTHERS.
>> BRAD SAYS IT DOES MAKE SENSE
TO KEEP PEOPLE AROUND THAT DO
HAVE A LOVED ONE.
I'M A LITTLE BIT MORE VULNERABLE
BECAUSE I HAVE NO LOVED ONE.
EVERYBODY LEFT ON THIS TRIBE HAS
A LOVED ONE EXCEPT FOR ME.
WHO KNOWS WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN, BUT I CAN DEFINITELY SEE
MYSELF IN TROUBLE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
GALANG GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW TADHANA TRIBE.
JOHN VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL,
CANDICE, MARISSA AND JOHN.
SO, CANDICE, BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
IN THE GAME, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHEN SOMEBODY'S COMING TO
REDEMPTION, CERTAINLY DON'T KNOW
WHO IS COMING.
WHAT WAS THE REACTION LAST NIGHT
WHEN YOUR HUSBAND WALKED IN?
>> UM, I WAS REALLY UPSET.
>> Jeff: UPSET SAD, UPSET MAD?
>> OH, JEFF, UPSET ALL, LIKE I
WANTED SOMEBODY TO COME THAT,
YOU KNOW, HE AND I COULD WORK
TOGETHER TO BEAT.
>> Jeff: SOMEBODY YOU COULD
HATE.
>> SOMEBODY I COULD HATE, LIKE
BRAD CULPEPPER.
>> JUST, YOU KNOW, LOOK AWAY.
YOU'RE A CHILD.
>> Jeff: MONOCASH EVERY TIME
WE COME HERE, YOUR HUSBAND GETS
DRILLED.
>> ALL I CAN SAY IS THERE'S NOT
JUST ONE PERSON VOTING.
THERE'S AN ENTIRE --
>> IT'S BEEN 8-1 AND 4-1.
>> WE'VE BEEN LISTENING TO THE
PEOPLE WHO GET VOTED OFF ABOUT
HOW HE'S SHUSHING THE WOMEN.
>> HAVE I SHUSHED A WOMAN?
ASK JOHN?
>> I DIDN'T SEE IT.
>> WHEN MARISSA CAME TO OUR
CAMP, SHE SAW ABOUT THIS MUCH...
>> ASK YOUR HUSBAND IF I'VE
HUSHED ANYBODY.
HAVE YOU HEARD ME HUSH ANYBODY?
>> DIDN'T HUSH ME.
>> HE DIDN'T HUSH A MAN THAT'S
BIGGER THAN HIM THAT CAN BEAT
HIS ASS.
>> I WILL SAY THAT ACCUSATIONS
ASIDE, EVERYBODY THAT'S BEEN
VOTED OUT AND SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND, EVERY SINGLE TIME IT'S
BEEN BRAD'S IDEA.
HE LIED TO ME ALL THE TIME, AND
HE'S NOT SOMEONE TO BE TRUSTED,
SO PEOPLE SHOULD START THINKING
ABOUT, THAT MAYBE START THINKING
ABOUT TRYING TO KNOCK THE KING
OFF HIS THRONE.
>> YOU MADE A WRONG DECISION IN
TRUSTING ME.
>> Jeff: ON MY GO, YOU'LL RACE
ACROSS THE LADDER BRIDGE WHILE
MANEUVERING A KEY.
WHEN YOU REACH THE END, USE THE
KEY TO UNLOCK A BAG.
THEN USE THE PIECES INSIDE TO
SOLVE A VERY COMPLICATED
SURVIVOR PUZZLE.
FIRST TWO TO FINISH STAY ALIVE,
LAST PERSON TO FINISH IS OUT FOR
GOOD.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER OF THIS
DUEL WILL DECIDE WHO GETS A CLUE
TO THE LOCATION OF THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
PICK YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
TWO WILL SURVIVE.
ONE WILL BE OUT FOR GOOD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GET UP ON THAT STRUCTURE.
JOHN OFF TO A FAST START.
MARISSA RIGHT THERE.
CANDICE IN IT.
YOU'RE MANEUVERING THAT KEY.
THAT KEY IS WHAT YOU NEED TO
UNLOCK THE BAG OF PUZZLE PIECES.
JOHN AND MARISSA NECK AND NECK.
CANDICE FALLING BEHIND A LITTLE
BIT.
MARISSA AT THE END.
SHE'S ALREADY WORKING ON HER
LOCK.
JOHN NOW WORKING ON HIS LOCK.
IT'S MARISSA AND JOHN.
JOHN HAS HIS BAG OF PUZZLE
PIECES FREE.
MARISSA HAS HER BAG FREE.
>> YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A COMPLICATED
"SURVIVOR" PUZZLE.
THE PUZZLE IS GOING TO TAKE YOU
A WHILE.
CANDICE HAS HER BAG OF PUZZLE
PIECES FREE.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLE NOW.
THIS WILL BE SQUARE WHEN IT IS
FINISHED.
THERE'S A SYMBOL ON TOP.
JOHN OFF TO A FAST START WITH
ANOTHER PIECE.
AND ANOTHER.
MARISSA OFF TO A QUICK START.
CANDICE SLOW AND STEADY,
SEPARATING HER PIECES.
JOHN ON A ROLL.
MARISSA WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> LET'S GO.
HERE WE GO.
>> Jeff: STARTING TO COME
TOGETHER.
CANDICE FALLING BEHIND A LITTLE
BIT.
YOU GOT TO PICK IT UP.
JOHN WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
JOHN STARTING TO PULL AWAY IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> COME ON, MARISSA.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
>> IT'S COMING TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: MARISSA PICKING UP
THE PACE NOW.
JOHN FLYING THROUGH THIS.
IT'S LIKE HE DESIGNED THIS
HIMSELF.
CANDICE PLACES A PIECE.
ALWAYS CALM UNLESS SHE'S YELLING
AT CULPEPPER.
>> YOU CUT MY BABY, I CUT YOU.
>> Jeff: JOHN CONTINUES HIS
PROGRESS WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> I THINK I CAN GET JOHN TO
LIKE ME AGAIN.
>> JOHN, RIGHT-HAND SIDE.
>> Jeff: OF ALL PEOPLE TO GIVE
JOHN A HAND, IT'S BRAD
CULPEPPER.
JOHN WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
JOHN GETTING VERY CLOSE TO
WINNING THIS.
JOHN CHECKING.
DOES HE HAVE IT RIGHT?
JOHN WINS THIS DUEL AND WILL
LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
CANDICE AND MARISSA NOW FIGHTING
FOR THAT SECOND SPOT.
IF YOU LOSE, YOU'RE DONE IN THIS
GAME.
MARISSA GETTING FRUSTRATED BY
THIS PUZZLE.
CANDICE'S METHODICAL APPROACH
STARTEDING TO PAY OFF.
>> HERE YOU GO, BABE.
>> Jeff: CANDICE WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
NOW CANDICE WITH A BIT OF A
LEAD.
MARISSA FALLING BEHIND.
>> LOOK AT JOHN.
HE'S ALREADY GOT THE TOP DONE.
>> IT'S NOT HELPING ME AT ALL.
>> Jeff: MARISSA QUICKLY
FALLING OUT OF THIS DUEL.
CANDICE GETTING CLOSER.
>> STOP, STOP, LOOK AT JOHN.
SEE HOW ALL HIS GRAY ARE ON THE
SAME SIDE?
THAT'S HOW YOURS SHOULD BE.
>> Jeff: CANDICE WITH ANOTHER
PIECE, GETTING DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
NOW.
CANDICE VERY CLOSE TO WINNING
THIS AND STAYING ALIVE.
IS SHE RIGHT?
CANDICE SURVIVES.
JOHN AND CANDICE, HUSBAND AND
WIFE, LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
MARISSA IS OUT OF THIS GAME.
[APPLAUSE]
JOHN, CANDICE, CONGRATULATIONS.
MARISSA, AFTER NINE DAYS IN THIS
GAME, YOUR SHOT AT THE $1
MILLION IS OVER.
GERVASE, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
YOUR NIECE'S EFFORTSES OUT HERE?
>> I'M IMPRESSED.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
KUDOS TO YOU.
YOU'VE JUST GIVEN ME A LITTLE
MORE OOMPH THAT I'VE NEEDED TO
GO FURTHER IN THIS GAME.
YOU KNOW HOW WE DO.
>> Jeff: MARISSA, YOUR TIME ON
SURVIVOR IS OVER.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
YOU CAN TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE
AIR.
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT, JOHN, IN ADDITION TO
STAYING ALIVE, YOU WON THIS
DUAL, WHICH MEANS YOU DECIDE WHO
GETS THE CLUE.
YOU CAN GIVE A CLUE TO ANYONE
YOU WANT ON ANY TRIBE FOR THE
LOCATION OF THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO GIVE IT TO?
>> JUST GIVE IT TO MONICA.
>> Jeff: DOES SHE TELL YOU
WHAT TO DO ALL THE TIME?
>> SHE DOES.
I DON'T ALWAYS LISTEN.
>> YES, THAT'S WHAT HUSBANDS AND
WIVES DO.
>> Jeff: WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
DO?
>> I'LL GIVE THE CLUE TO MONICA.
>> Jeff: WHY?
>> SPREAD IT AROUND.
THERE WAS A TARGET ON MY BACK.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE TRYING TO
GET RID OF A CULPEPPER.
>> WE'RE REALLY NOT INTERESTED.
>> WALK IT DOWN AND PUT IT IN
THE FIRE.
>> I DON'T THINK OUR TRIBE IS
INTERESTED.
>> EVERYBODY RECOGNIZES AT THIS
POINT THAT WHEN YOU GET THAT
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE THE
TARGET IS ON YOUR BACK.
MONICA VERY SMARTLY BURNED IT.
>> THAT'S THE FIRST TIME THAT
HAS EVER HAPPENED.
>> DOING WHAT SHE'S TOLD.
>> NOT ONLY DOES MONICA NOT WANT
IT, SHE BURNS IT SO NOBODY ELSE
WILL HAVE IT.
WE'RE DONE HERE.
YOU TWO STAY ALIVE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD BACK TO
REDEMPTION AND AWAIT YOUR NEXT
DUEL.
>> WHY NOT JUST THROW IT AWAY?
I'M IN A GOOD POSITION OVER
HERE, BUT IT WORRIES THAT
CONSTANTLY WHEN I GO TO DUELS
PEOPLE ARE SO AGGRESSIVE TOWARDS
MY HUSBAND.
>> IT WOULD BE GREAT TO BE
REDEEMED AND HANG AROUND WITH
YOU.
>> THE SILVER LINING TO GETTING
VOTED OFF MY TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND IS I CAME OUT
INTO THIS GAME THE PLAY WITH
CANDICE.
IN A WEIRD WAY I SHOULD THANK
BRAD AND THE REST OF MY TRIBE
FOR GIVING ME THE OPPORTUNITY TO
HANG OUT WITH MY WIFE ON THIS
BEAUTIFUL BEACH AND STILL BE IN
THE GAME AND ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
WIN DUELS AND I GET BACK IN.
>> THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
>> YOU'RE JEALOUS I CAUGHT MORE
THAN YOU.
>> I'M NOT JEALOUS.
I'M STOKED.
I'M HUNGRY.
>> THIS WILL BE A FUN STORY TO
TELL THE KIDS ONE DAY.
AND IN THE END, IF HE WIN,
FABULOUS.
IF I WIN, FABULOUS.
>> I REALLY WANTED TO PLAY THE
GAME WITH YOU.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO DO IT LIKE
THIS.
>> I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S LIKE, CAN'T ANYBODY SEE
THAT THE ULTIMATE SACRIFICE IS
BEING MADE BY THE LOVED ONES ON
THE OTHER SIDE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
IF ANYBODY HAS ANY LOGIC THAT
THEY CAN BESTOW UPON ME, I'D
APPRECIATE IT.
IT'S HARD TO SEE.
>> I JUST THINK IT'S... PEOPLE
HAVE HURT FEELINGS AND THEY'RE
BITTER AND MAD.
>> IF I KNOW BRAD, HE'S UP
FIRST, HE'S GOT THE FIRE GOING,
HE'S MAKING SURE EVERYBODY HAS
WATER.
HE'S CATCHING FISH, HE'S DOING
EVERYTHING THAT HE CAN TO MAKE
IT EASIER FOR OUR LOVED ONES ON
THE OTHER SIDE, AND I GUESS THAT
JUST PUTS A TARGET ON YOUR BACK.
>> IS THERE EVER GOING TO BE A
DUEL THAT MY HUSBAND IS NOT
VERBALLY ACCOSTED BY A BUNCH OF
PEOPLE THAT DON'T EVEN KNOW HIM?
SHOOTING SOMEONE A BIRD THAT YOU
DON'T EVEN KNOW JUST SEEMS...
>> IT'S HARD TO WATCH.
>> YOU KNOW, LEADERS HAVE
FOLLOWERS, AND IF THAT'S THE
CASE, THEN SOMEBODY'S BUYING
WHAT HE'S SELLING, BUT BRAD IS
THE STRONGEST ONE OUT HERE.
IF HE MAKES IT TO THE MERGE, I
WON'T BELIEVE IT.
>> THE ONLY THING I HAVE TO SAY
IS YOU KNOW BRAD AS BRAD CULL
PEPER FROM TAMPA.
YOU DON'T KNOW BRAD FROM
SURVIVOR.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING TO YOU FOR
YOU JUST TO OPEN YOUR EYES JUST
A LITTLE BIT.
EVEN IF HE'S JUST A LITTLE BIT
DEVIOUS, THAT'S PART OF THE
GAME.
HE GOT RID OF RISK CENTENNIAL
PARK KUDOS FOR HIM.
THEY'RE PLAYING THE GAME.
THAT'S HOW I LOOK AT IT.
I GUESS YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
YOUR LOVED ONE IS THE ONE THAT
IS THE BAD GUY, QUOTE/UNQUOTE,
THAT'S GETTING RID OF PEOPLE,
BUT SOMEBODY HAS TO BE.
ONE OF OUR LOVED ONES IS RUNNING
THE SHOW.
I KNOW IT'S NOT MINE, SO IT'S
SOMEBODY ELSE'S, BUT KUDOS TO
YOU.
>> WELL, THANK YOU FOR THE
SUPPORT.
I APPRECIATE IT.
AND I WON'T LET YOU GUYS DOWN
OVER HERE, THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> I JUST LOVE THAT CANDICE
CALLED MONICA OUT ON THE
QUOTE/UNQUOTE DOING WHAT BRAD
SAYS WHEN CANDICE WAS THE ONE
WHO SAID, "GIVE IT TO MONICA."
>> YOU GOING TO DO WHAT YOUR MAN
SAYS?
>> TODAY IS A ROUGH DAY.
I WASN'T EXPECTING CANDICE TO BE
SO PERSONAL.
>> LIKE YOU GIRLS DO WHATEVER
YOU'RE TOLD.
>> OH, YOU GOING TO DO WHAT YOUR
MAN SAYS?
EVERYONE ASSUMES I'M THE GRAND
POOH-BAH.
IT'S NATURAL FOR ME TO LEAD MY
FAMILY.
I HAVE BECOME LEADER OF THIS
GROUP.
>> THEY'RE MAD IF WE VOTE OUT A
LOVED ONE AND SOMEBODY'S MAD
WHEN WE DON'T.
>> NOBODY'S MAD AT YOU GUYS.
THEY'RE MAD AT ME.
>> THINKING AHEAD, SHOULD WE
LOSE THE NEXT CHALLENGE, CALEB
IS UNCONNECTED, AND I COULD SEND
A MESSAGE TO THE OTHER SIDE THAT
WE'RE WANTING TO PLAY BALL WITH
YOU GUYS, AND IT ALSO TAKES SOME
HEAT OFF ME AT REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
IF CALEB ROLLS OUT THERE ON THE
ARENA FLOOR, NOBODY'S GOING TO
BE SCREAMING AT ME.
I'VE BEEN A TARGETS MY WHOLE
LIFE.
THIS IS NOTHING NEW.
>> IT'S TURNED INTO NOT
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IT'S THE BRAD BASHING HOUR.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
BRAD IS PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER ONE.
WE SEE THAT EVERY TIME WE'VE
BEEN TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> IT'S WEIRD BECAUSE I KNOW HE
JUST TOTALLY SCHANKED JOSH.
>> SCHANKED HIM SO HARD.
>> IT'S GOOD FOR US TO KEEP BRAD
SO WHEN WE GET THE MERGE, IT
TAKES THE HEAT OFF OF US.
>> IF WE DO LOSE AND WE HAVE TO
GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, IT'S GOING
TO BE ONE OF THE GIRLS GOING
OUT.
>> BUT WE ALSO GOT TO MAKE SURE
HE DON'T GET JOHN.
>> I THINK ME, HAYDEN AND VYTAS
ARE PRETTY SOLID.
BRAD'S THE LOW MAN ON THE
>> I KEEP TRYING TO DO NORMAL
STUFF WITH IT AND THEN I
REMEMBER...
>> NOT A GOOD IDEA.
>> YEAH, THAT IT'S IN PAIN.
>> TAKE IT EASY, MAN.
I'M GOING TO GO GET SOME WOOD.
TYSON, STAY DOWN.
>> I'LL STAY HERE.
>> DEEFL DON'T HELP.
I WANT YOU TO REST.
>> I HURT MY SHOULDER AT THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
EVERY DAY IT GETS A LITTLE BIT
BETTER, BUT I DO LIKE TO PLAY IT
UP A LITTLE BIT BECAUSE THEN I
HAVE TO DO LESS WORK AROUND
CAMP.
HOPEFULLY THAT ALSO KEEPS THEM
IN SYMPATHY WITH ME.
ARE THEY OUT FAR ENOUGH?
>> YEAH.
LET'S GO THIS WAY.
>> ME AND GERVASE, WE HAVE A
THING GOING WHERE WE SNEAK OFF
AND DRINK A COUPLE COCONUTS.
WE'VE BEEN OPENING THEM A
DIFFERENT WAY SO PEOPLE WOULDN'T
REALIZE WE'VE BEEN CHOPPING
THEM.
I WOULD REALLY LIKE THE KEEP
EATING THOSE COCONUTS.
I CAN'T WAIT UNTIL THEY WRING
ALL THOSE COCONUTS DOWN AND JUST
EXAMINE EACH AND EVERY ONE OF
THEM.
>> THE COCONUT BANDITS ARE BACK.
>> THEY ALL HAVE LITTLE CUTS.
THEY ALL HAVE THE LITTLE...
>> THEY'VE BEEN EATING THEM.
>> I KNOW.
>> THEY ALL HAVE THAT.
>> WE SHOULD LEAVE THEM.
>> RUPERT'S LAW, CANNOT GET
COCONUT OFF THE BRAIN.
I THOUGHT OUR COVER WAS BLOWN
RIGHT THEN AND THERE.
I THOUGHT, OH, MAN, HOW ARE WE
GETTING TO EXPLAIN THAT.
>> HAS THAT BEEN EATEN OR DOES
IT HAVE A CRACK IN IT.
>> OH, IT DOES.
NO WONDER.
>> THEN MONICA'S LIKE, IT'S
PROBABLY A CRAB.
THANK YOU, MONOCAMP
>> CAN'T THE CRAB JUST SHARE A
COCONUT.
>> SO FAR SO GOOD.
OPERATION COCONUT IS STILL
RUNNING SMOOTH.
IF EVERYBODY KNEW ABOUT IT,
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO GET PISSED,
SO I'M KEEPING THIS TO
OURSELVES.
ME AND TYSON, WHO WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT.
>> MOST OF THE COCONUTS ARE LIKE
THAT.
THEY'RE DRILLED INTO.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY DORK
THEY DIG INTO IT.
>> THEN THEY EAT IT AND
OBVIOUSLY THE MILK IS SPOILED.
>> I'M DEFINITELY WITH GERVASE
RIGHT NOW.
IF THAT LASTS THROUGH TO THE
FINALS, SO BE IT.
IT WOULD DEFINITELY BE IN
GERVASE' BEST INTERESTS TO STICK
WITH ME, AS WELL, BECAUSE WE
BOTH LOST OUR LOVED ONE IN THE
GAME.
ARAS STILL HAS HIS.
IF VYTAS MAKES IT TO THE MERGE,
HE'LL WORK WITH VYTAS.
THEY'RE THE STRONGEST CONSUME
CUMULATIVELY, SO TO HAVE THEM
BOTH I THINK IS A HUGE DANGER.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, I WILL TAKE
BACK THE IDOL ONCE AGAIN.
>> YOU CAN JUST LEAVE IT HERE,
JEFF.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
ON MY GO, YOU WILL PADDLE OUT TO
A SERIES OF CRATES.
YOU'LL DIVE DOWN, RELEASE THE
CRATE, PUT IT IN YOUR BOAT.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL FIVE, YOU'LL
USE THEM TO BUILD A STAIRCASE.
TWO TRIBE MEMBERS MUST THEN
SOLVE THE PUZZLE REVEALING THE
COMBINATION THAT RELEASES THE
KEY.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO FIND THE
RIGHT KEY CAN USE IT TO RAISE
THEIR FLAG AND WIN IMMUNITY.
YOU'RE SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> ALL: YES.
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TRIBE,
TEA AND COFFEE, CROISSANT,
BUSINESS -- BISCOTTI.
LIGHT THOSE TASTEBUDS UP WITH
SOMETHING THEY HAVEN'T HAD FOR A
WHILE.
OR IF YOU LIKE YOU CAN TRADE IT
FOR FISHING GEAR.
GALANG HAS IT.
THEY KNOW HOW VALUABLE IT IS.
TADHANA MAY CHOOSE THAT.
GALANG TWO EXTRA MEMBERS, IT
ISING TWO PEOPLE OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
TINA AND KAT GOING TO SIT OUT
FOR GALANG.
TYSON WITH YOUR ARM IN A SLING,
YOU FEEL YOU'RE MORE HELPFUL IN
WHAT IS CLEARLY GOING TO BE A
STRENUOUS CHALLENGE THAN TINA OR
KAT?
>> I CAN DO IT.
>> MY SHOULDER DOES STILL HURT,
BUT IT IS GETTING BETTER EVERY
DAY.
THE THING, IS I'M BETTER THAN
MOST EVERYBODY ON MY TRIBE WITH
ONE ARM, SO I WANT TO WIN.
>> TINA, KAT, TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY.
GO!
GET THAT BOAT IN THE WATER.
>> LET'S GO, GALANG.
WILL REST GO.
>> Jeff: TADHANA WORKING WELL
TOGETHER.
>> TURN IT.
>> PADDLE.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> Jeff: GALANG IN EARLY
TROUBLE.
TADHANA WITH AN EARLY LEAD.
JUST LIKE THEY'VE HAD IN SO MANY
CHALLENGES.
BUT THEY HAVE YET TO DELIVER A
WIN.
IT'S GOT TO GO AROUND YOUR FLAG
TO YOUR FIRST CRATE.
>> FORWARD, FORWARD!
>> I'M READY, BABY.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN IN THE WATER
FOR TADHANA.
GALANG STILL HAS TO GET OUT AND
AROUND THEIR FLAG BEFORE THEY
CAN EVEN START.
HAYDEN HAS RELEASED THE FIRST
CRATE FOR TADHANA.
GALANG IS NOW PASSED THEIR FLAG.
THEY CAN START WORKING ON THEIR
FIRST CRATE.
LAURA IN THE WATER.
TADHANA HAS THEIR FIRST CRATE,
HEADING TO THE SECOND ONE.
BRAD IN THE WATER FOR TADHANA.
LAURA QUICKLY RELEASES THAT
CRATE.
IN RECORD TIME.
TADHANA CONTINUES WITH ITS LEAD.
CULPEPPER HAS THE SECOND CRATE
FOR TADHANA.
THEY'RE HEADING OUT NOW TO THEIR
THIRD.
IT'S MONICA NOW IN THE WATER FOR
THE SECOND CRATE FOR GALANG.
CULPEPPER GOING TO GO AGAIN FOR
TADHANA.
MONICA CULPEPPER COMING UP FOR
GALANG.
SHE'S RELEASED THE SECOND CRATE.
BRAD CULPEPPER UP WITH THE THIRD
CRATE FOR TADHANA.
TADHANA NEARLY TIPS THEIR BOAT.
THESE CRATES WEIGH A LOT.
LAURA WITH ANOTHER CRATE.
GALANG HAS THEIR THIRD CRATE.
CULPEPPER HAS ANOTHER CRATE FOR
TADHANA.
TADHANA WITH FOUR CRATES.
GALANG WITH THREE.
THERE ARE FIVE TOTAL.
MONICA CULPEPPER BACK IN THE
WATER.
TADHANA HEADING FOR THAT FIFTH
AND FINAL CRATE.
BRAD CULPEPPER IN THE WATER
AGAIN.
GALANG HAS THEIR FOURTH CRATE.
THE CULL PEPPERS HAVE DOMINATED
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
BRAD WITH ANOTHER GREAT EFFORT
UNDER WATER HAS FIFTH AND FINAL
CRATE FOR TADHANA.
GALANG LOOKING FOR THAT FIFTH
AND FINAL CRATE.
LAURA BACK IN THE WATER AGAIN.
TADHANA LOSES TWO CRATES IN THE
WATER.
DISASTER FOR TADHANA, OPENING
THE DOOR FOR GALANG, WHO NOW HAS
THEIR FIFTH CRATE.
THEY CAN HEAD BACK.
HAYDEN IN THE WATER TRYING TO
RETRIEVE A CRATE.
GALANG WAS BEHIND, NOW HAS THE
LEAD.
TADHANA HAS THEIR FIVE CRATES
BACK IN.
GALANG IS BACK WITH ALL FIVE.
START UNLOADING THOSE CRATES UP
ON THE DECK.
TADHANA NOW WORKING THEIR WAY
BACK.
TADHANA SQUANDERED A HUGE LEAD.
>> GO GO,, GO GO, GO, GO,.
>> Jeff: TADHANA IS BACK.
THEY'RE LOSING THE CRATES.
YOU GOT TO GET ALL FIVE CRATES
UP ON THE DECK BEFORE YOU CAN
START BUILDING THE STAIRCASE.
>> GOOD JOB.
GREAT JOB.
>> Jeff: GET 'EM UP HERE.
LET'S GO.
KEEP MOVING.
GO!
>> GO, GO.
>> Jeff: GO, TADHANA, GET THAT
ROPE OFF THERE.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THE
STAIRCASE NOW.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST ONE HERE.
THIS HAS TO BE.
>> Jeff: DWAL -- GALANG
WORKING TOGETHER.
THEY THINK THEY HAVE SOMETHING.
>> THIS IS THE BEGINNING, I
PROMISE YOU.
>> Jeff: IT WILL SPELL OUT
BLOOD VERSUS WATER ON THE SIDE.
YOU'LL KNOW IF IT'S RIGHT.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK.
GALANG HAS NOT LOST A SINGLE
CHALLENGE THIS SEASON.
>> THIS IS THE VERY TOP.
>> Jeff: TADHANA HAS NOT WON
ONE.
BOTH TRIBES GETTING CLOSER.
>> WE GOT IT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT IT.
TADHANA HAS IT.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
>> GO, GO GO, GO, GO,.
>> Jeff: GALANG HAS IT.
IT IS VYTAS AND CIERA AND TYSON
AND LAUREN.
LAST TIME CIERA WENT UP AGAINST
HER MOM IN A PUZZLE, HER MOM
WON.
CIERA WOULD LOVE A VICTORY HERE.
THE PUZZLE IS A COMBINATION THAT
YOU NEED TO RELEASE THE KEY.
THAT KEY WILL OPEN YOUR LOCK,
ALLOWING YOU TO RAISE YOUR
TRIBE'S FLAG AND CELEBRATE A
VICTORY.
THIS CHALLENGE HAS BEEN BACK AND
FORTH.
GALANG WAS TRAILING.
NOW BACK IN THE LEAD.
>> RIGHT THERE, RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: TADHANA'S GOING TO
HAVE TO PICK IT UP.
>> WHAT IS THAT WORD?
>> GALANG GETTING VERY CLOSE TO
FINISHING THEIR PUZZLE.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED THE
LAST TIME LAURA SHOWED DOWN
AGAINST HER DAUGHTER CIERA.
>> COME ON, CIERA.
>> COME ON, GALANG.
>> Jeff: GALANG HAS THEIR
PUZZLE SOLVED.
START WORKING ON THE
COMBINATION.
TADHANA'S GOT THE KEEP MOVING.
>> GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: TYSON THINKS THEY
HAVE IT SOLVED.
GALANG CAN SMELL VICTORY AGAIN.
TADHANA STILL STRUGGLING.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: TYSON UNTIES THE KEY.
TYSON HEADING UP.
IF HE'S RIGHT, GALANG WINS AND
REMAINS UNDEFEATED.
IS HE RIGHT?
AND HE IS.
GALANG WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD
AND REMAINS UNDEFEATED IN
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. WATER."
>> GREAT JOB, GREAT JOB, GREAT
JOB!
>> I WANT CIERA TO SUCCEED,
BECAUSE YOU WANT YOUR KIDS TO
SUCCEED SO BAD, AND YOU WANT
THEM TO WIN, BUT YET I HAVE A
TRIBE OF PEOPLE THAT ARE
COUNTING ON ME, AS WELL.
I KNEW SHE COULDN'T BEAT ME.
AND SHE COULD BE GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: GALANG, ANOTHER
VICTORY.
YOU HAVE YET TO BE WITHOUT THIS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL AGAIN TONIGHT.
IN ADDITION, NICE REWARD.
COME GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK
THE CAMP, ENJOY IT.
TADHANA, TRIBAL COUNCIL ONCE
AGAIN, WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT OF YOUR TRIBE AND SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK THE
CAMP.
YOU KNOW THE ROUTINE.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL TONIGHT.
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
WE HAVEN'T WON YET.
I MEAN, WE SUCK.
AND IT'S SO DISHEARTENING, TOO,
BECAUSE CLEARLY WE'RE A BIGGER,
STRONGER, MORE ATHLETIC TEAM,
BUT TODAY WE LOST TO A ONE-ARMED
DUDE AND THREE MOMS.
THAT'S BRUTAL.
BRUTAL.
>> I'M COMING.
>> AFTER A LOSS IT'S ALWAYS A
ROUTINE.
THE GUYS WILL GO GET WATER,
WHICH IS CODE FOR GO STRATEGIZE
AGAINST THE GIRLS, AND THE GIRLS
MAKE RICE, WHICH IS CODE FOR HOW
DO WE SAVE OUR ASSES.
TODAY WAS INTERESTING.
>> SO IT'S A NO-BRAINER.
CALEB.
I RECKON YOU GUYS WANT TO
BELIEVE ME.
>> BRAD SAID, I'M VOTING CALEB.
SO THEN I'M LIKE, OKAY.
WELL BRAD COULD BE TELLING THE
TRUTH OR HE MIGHT NOT BE, BUT
I'M GOING TO ACT LIKE I BELIEVE
HIM.
I SAT THERE AND SAID, YES, I
BELIEVE YOU 100%, BUT REALLY DO
I?
>> IF WE DO ANOTHER CHALLENGE
AND WE LOSE, YOU KNOW, THEN IT'S
NUT-CUTTING TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> BRAD?
>> YOU COMING?
>> YEAH, I AM.
>> I'M NOT LYING TO YOU.
>> I LOVE CIERA, BUT SHE'S
WORTHLESS.
>> THAT'S THE SECOND PUZZLE THAT
CICI'S NOT BEEN THAT STRONG ON.
HAYDEN AND VYTAS AND MYSELF WERE
ALL ON BOARD WITH VOTING CIERA.
THAT'S WHAT WE WENT TO DISCUSS.
WHEN BRAD NEVER SHOWED UP BEHIND
US, I STARTED THINKING, WHAT
KIND OF STUNT COULD BRAD BE
WORKING ON BECAUSE WE ALL WENT
TO THE WELL AND BRAD STAYED
BEHIND WITH THE TWO GIRL, SO IT
WAS A LITTLE FISHY.
WE JUST GOT RID OF JOHN, SO AS
EASY AS IT WENT DOWN FROM FIVE
GUYS TO FOUR GUYS, IT COULD JUST
AS EASILY GO DOWN TO THREE GUYS.
>> I GOT THE GIRLS CONVINCED
IT'S CALEB.
>> I REALLY THINK CIERA TONIGHT.
>> YOU THINK CIERA?
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE I DON'T TRUST BRAD
100%, I FEEL CONFIDENT IN HAYDEN
AND VYTAS THEY'LL HAVE MY BACK,
SO CIERA SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> AS THE DE FACTO LEADER HERE,
I HAVE TO MAKE SOME DECISIONS.
I TALK TO THE GIRL, THEY'RE
OBVIOUSLY IN FOR VOTING OFF
CALEB.
BUT CIERA IS TERRIBLE ON THE
CHALLENGE.
GETTING RID OF HER WILL MAKE
THIS TRIBE STRONGER.
GOING BEYOND ALL THE LOVE
CONNECTIONS AND EVERYTHING ELSE,
I WANT THE MAKE THE TRIBE
STRONG, SO I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT
REDEMPTION ISLAND AND THE HEAT I
WILL TAKE.
I'M SURE IF CIERA SHOWS UP, I'LL
TAKE HEAT FROM HER MOM.
DOESN'T MATTER, CIERA'S GOING
HOME.
>> Jeff: SO BRAD, WHEN YOU SIT
AT HOME AND FANTASIZE ABOUT
PLAYING "SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. "ST
HOW IT GOES?
>> NO, THIS IS NOT HOW I
ENVISIONED IT.
SOME CHALLENGES WE LOSE ON
STRENGTH.
TWO WE LOST ON PUZZLES.
CIERA VOLUNTEERED FOR BOTH OF
THOSE AND WE LOVES.
>> Jeff: SO CIERA, DID YOU GO
BACK THE CAMP FEELING, MAYBE
THEY SHOULD VOTE ME OUT?
>> WELL, THERE'S A SENSE OF
LIKE, OKAY, CIERA, MAYBE YOU
AREN'T AT GOOD AS PUZZLES AS YOU
THINK YOU ARE OBVIOUSLY, BUT AT
THE SAME TIME, I'M NOT GOING TO
SIT AROUND AND BITCH ABOUT IT
AND SIT THERE AND WINE AND GIVE
UP AND VOTE ME OUT.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO FIGURE OUR
WHERE CAN I BENEFIT SOMEBODY,
TRY TO FIGURE OUT OPTIONS AND
WHERE TO GO.
>>
>> Jeff: BRAD, AT EVERY
REDEMPTION ISLAND DUEL, YOU TAKE
GRIEF FOR WHO THIS TRIBE VOTES
OUT.
>> YEAH.
AND IT'S TOUGH WHEN YOU GOT YOUR
DIRTY LAUNDRY GETTING AIRED.
THE STUFF THEY'RE SAYING IS
INCORRECT YET THE OTHER TRIBE
DOESN'T KNOW THAT.
THEY'RE ASSUMING IT'S CORRECT.
AND UNLIKE "SURVIVOR" PAST, GO
HAVE LOVED ONES ON THE OTHER
SIDE, SO IF YOU IGNORE THAT,
YOU'RE NOT DOING WHAT'S SMART IN
THIS "SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS.
WATER."
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE SAYING IT
WOULD BE GREAT TO VOTE OUT
SOMEBODY WITHOUT A LOVED ONE
BECAUSE NOBODY FROM THE OTHER
TRIBE WILL BE MAD.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S A VALID POINT.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
IT WOULD BE A LOT EASIER
TOMORROW, YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO
WEIGH IT ALL IN.
AND DON'T THINK THAT WASN'T
FACTOR IN TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHO IS THE BEST ONE TO GO HOME.
>> CALEB, DID YOU FEEL THAT
PRESSURE?
>> I DID FEEL THAT PRESSURE.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT'S THE "THE BD
SIDE," THE TASTE IN THE MOUTH
AND YOU WANT MORE OF IT.
I LOVE A BLINDSIDE, DO I WANT TO
BE THE BUTT OF IT?
NO, I DON'T.
I WAS FINE BEING THE GOAT.
WHEN WE TELL SOMEBODY WE'RE
VOTING AND WE'RE REALLY NOT, BUT
THAT'S WHERE IT SHOULD HAVE
ENDED INSTEAD OF ME FEELING LIKE
THE CALF BEING LED TO SLAUGHTER.
SO I'M OBVIOUSLY THE LOW MAN ON
THE TOTEM POLE.
>> NO, NO, YOU'RE NOT.
>> BUT YOU CAMPAIGNED AGAINST ME
TODAY.
>> I DIDN'T CAMPAIGN AGAINST
YOU.
THERE WAS CONVERSATION.
CAMPAIGN IS A BAD WORD.
I WASN'T CAMPAIGNING AGAINST
YOU.
>> HAYDEN, NOW YOU HAVE A REAL
PROBLEM.
CALEB HAS A BAD TASTE IN HIS
MOUTH.
>> DEFINITELY IT'S GOING TO
CREATE SOME CRACKS.
WE HAVE SOME PATCH WORK TO DO.
THE PROBLEM IS ONCE YOU DISTRUST
SOMEBODY, IT'S REALLY HARD TO
REGAIN THEIR TRUST, ESPECIALLY
IN A GAME LIKE THIS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: CALEB, WHAT DOES THIS
TRIBE NEED TO DO TO GET YOUR
TRUST BACK BECAUSE YOU DO HAVE A
VALUE, WITHOUT A LOVED ONE, YOU
CAN GO ANYWHERE YOU WANT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I TRUST VYTAS AND HAYDEN.
BRAD IS ON THE FENCE RIGHT NOW.
THE WAY THAT I'M FEELING, I
DON'T WANT YOU TO GO HOME.
I'M GOING TO WRITE BRAD'S NAME
DOWN.
YOU ALL CAN DO WHAT YOU WANT TO,
BUT THAT'S THREE UP FRONT AND
THE GUYS BACK THERE, YOU ALL CAN
DECIDE WHAT YOU ALL WANT TO DO.
>> Jeff: WOW.
CIERA, THAT'S THROWING IT OUT
THERE.
>> OH, MY GOSH, IT'S LIKE YOU
COME INTO THIS GAME AND YOU MAKE
THIS WHOLE PLAN OUT, AND THEN
THIS HAPPENS.
SO I THINK THAT NOBODY SHOULD
FEEL COMFORTABLE AND EVERYBODY
SHOULD FEEL ON EDGE IN THIS GAME
AND YOU JUST HAVE TO JUST ROLL
WITH IT.
>> I'M NOT WRITING YOUR NAME
DOWN, CALEB.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> YOU CAN WRITE MY NAME DOWN, I
UNDERSTAND, BUT I'M NOT
>> I'M JUST SHOCKED THAT CALEB
WILL BE WRITING BRAD'S NAME
DOWN.
>> UH-HUH.
>> WOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WOW.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING YOU
ALL.
IT'S UP TO YOU ALL.
THE BALL'S IN YOU ALL'S COURT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
THE CHALLENGES BRAD TAKES THE
REINS.
IT'S NOT HIM.
WE ALL DEGREE, BUT MAYBE THERE'S
ANOTHER PROBLEM.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO DO THAT?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO DO THAT, NO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CALEB, YOU'RE UP.
>> SORRY, DUDE.
YOU MESS WITH THE BULL, YOU GET
THE HORNS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, BRAD.
CIERA.
BRAD.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CIERA, TWO
VOTES BRAD, ONE VOTE LEFT.
BRAD.
WE HAVE A TIE.
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING TO WORK.
WE'RE GOING TO REVOTE.
BRAD AND CIERA, YOU WILL NOT
VOTE.
THE OTHER FOUR, YOU CAN ONLY
VOTE FOR BRAD OR CIERA.
CALEB, YOU WANT THE GRAB THIS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL, THE PERSON
VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE BRAD.
CIERA.
BRAD.
TWO VOTES BRAD.
ONE VOTE CIERA.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR" BLOOD VERSUS WATER,
BRAD.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
I'M NOT ANGRY.
GOOD LUCK.
I'LL TRY TO GET BACK INCH I'M
NOT MAD AT YOU.
I MADE A BAD MOVE.
>> Jeff: BRAD, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE CHANCE TO GET BACK
IN THIS GAME.
>> I'LL TRY.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR TORCH AND
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
>> THAT'S GOING TO BE FUN.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> Jeff: WELL, THAT WAS ONE OF
THE MOST SHOCKING VOTES AND
POTENTIALLY ONE OF THE BIGGEST
SHIFTS OF POWER THAT'S EVER
HAPPENED AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND
HOPEFULLY IT'S EXACTLY WHAT THIS
TRIBE NEEDS.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK THE CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions and CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> I CAN KIND OF CONTROL THIS
GAME RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: AFTER BLOWING UP
TRIBAL COUNCIL, CALEB'S READY TO
MAKE SOME MORE NOISE.
>> DO I FEEL POWERFUL NOW?
I THINK THE WORD IS "BIG
KAHUNA."
>> Jeff: AND THE CULPEPPERS
ARE LOOKING TO MAKE A MOVE OF
THEIR OWN.
>> CAN I TAKE YOUR SPOT?
>> JOHN AN CANDICE, BEFORE YOU
GUYS HIT ME, I WAVE THE WHITE
FLAG.
>> I WAS DEAD ASLEEP AND I HEAR
THE SWEETEST VOICE I EVER WANTED
TO HEAR ON REDEMPTION ISLAND,
BRAD CULPEPPER.
NOW I HAVE MY CHANCE TO PUT HIM
OUT OF THE GAME FOR GOOD.