LAST WEEK ON
"SURVIVOR": WE ARE MERGED.
AFTER THE TRIBES MERGE, THE
RETURNING PLAYERS AND LOVED ONES
WERE FINALLY REUNITED.
>> THIS IS WHERE "SURVIVOR"
REALLY BECOME "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: BACK AT CAMP, TYSON
FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I'M DEFINITELY NOT SHARING
THIS WITH ANYBODY ELSE.
>> Jeff: AND TWO PAIRS OF
LOVED ONE, ARAS AND VYTAS, AND
TINA AND KATIE THOUGHT THEY WERE
SITTING PERFECT.
>>.
BUT THAT WAS FAR FROM THE TRUTH.
>> YOU'RE WITH US.
WOO TAKE ARAS OUT FIRST.
>> Jeff: EXPAT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
ARAS WAS THE VICTIM OF A VIRS
BLINDSIDE.
>> ARAS, YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
>> WELL PLAYED, GUYS, WELL
PLAYED.
>> Jeff: ARAS, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
10 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> WELL, YOU GUYS, THAT WAS A
GREAT MOVE.
AS A FAN OF THE SHOCK, ARAS DID
NOT SEE THAT COMING, MAN,
NEITHER DID I.
SO CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
IT SUCKS TO SEE MY BRO GO,
THOUGH, I WILL SAY THAT.
>> I LOVED ARAS, TOO, WE ALL
DID.
>> HEY, HEY, IT'S THE GAME, MAN.
>> ARAS MYSELF AND TINA AND
KATIE GOT COMPLETELY BLINDSIDED.
VENGEANCE IS GOING TO BE MINE AT
SOME POINT.
KNIVES OUT, BRO.
LET'S GET IT ON AND I WILL SEE
HOW BAD I CAN GET YOU.
>> WELL, I CAN'T KEEP MY MOUTH
SHUT.
SO I'VE GOTTA SAY SOMETHING.
BRAVO TO YOU.
THAT WAS A GREAT MOVE.
MONICA AND TYSON, YOU WON THE
BATTLE.
BUT YOU DIDN'T WIN THE WAR.
BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT FIVE JURY
VOTES THAT YOU'LL NEVER GET FOR
FLIPPING.
AND--
>> TINA?
>> WHAT?
>> YOU, KATIE, AND VETEAS PUSHED
US OUT.
>> I DIDN'T PUSH ANYBODY OUT.
>> WELL, THAT WAS ARAS' PLAN.
>> I DON'T KNOW THAT THAT WAS
HIS PLAN.
BUT THE THING IS, THAT YOU ALL
WERE NEVER IN THE ALLIANCE.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I HAD AN ALLIANCE WITH ARAS.
>> HAD AN ALLIANCE WITH ARASA
WELL.
>> WE ALL DID, TINA.
>> EVERY PERSON?
EVERYBODY?
>> YES, FIVE.
>> THAT'S THE CRAZIEST PART,
TINA--
>> LOOK, WE ALL FELT LIKE WE
WERE HIS TOP THREE.
THERE WAS ONE PERSON THAT WAS
FLIPPING ON EVERYBODY, AND HE'S
OUT OF THE GAME RIGHT NOW.
>> UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> AND YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND
THAT.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> BECAUSE YOU ACCUSED ME OF
SOMETHING I AM NOT GUILTY OF.
"SURVIVOR'S" BROKEN MY HEART
TWICE, AND I THINK TONIGHT I
FELL BACK IN LOVE.
I KNEW ARAS WASN'T GOING TO TAKE
ME TO THE END, AND I KNEW TINA
HAD PRIORITIZED KATY IN FRONT OF
ME, SO FOR HER TO COME OUT AND
SAY, "YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF
YOURSELF BECAUSE THAT'S NOT THE
WAY I PLAY THE GAME," OOIK LIME,
"TINA, IF EVERYONE PLAYED THE
GAME YOU DO, I WOULD WIN 100% OF
THE TIME."
>> NOT LOOKING GOOD FOR THE HOME
TEAM, AND I REALLY AM SORRY.
THE THING SI CHOSE WHICH
ALLIANCE I WAS GOING TO GO WITH,
AND I STUCK WITH IT.
AND IT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
BUT THAT'S JUST MY GAME.
>> IT PUTS US ON THE OUTS.
>> YEAH, ME, YOU, AND VETEAS.
YOU NEED TO FURTHER YOUR GAME
BECAUSE I'VE GOT A MUCH, MUCH
BIGGER TARGET ON ME.
DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE TO PULL
ME INTO ANYTHING.
IF YOU CAN FURTHER YOURSELF IN
THE GAME, PLEASE, DO SO.
I WANT THAT FOR YOU.
>> MY MOM MENTIONED THAT I NEED
TO HAVE A GAME PLAN BECAUSE IF
TRIBAL HAPPENS AND I'M A SITTING
DUCK, IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
PRETTY.
SO SHE TOLD ME TO TRY TO BUILD
MY OWN INDIVIDUAL ALLIANCE AND
TALK TO PEOPLE AND SELL MY VOTE.
HOW I DO SELL MYSELF WHEN I HAVE
MY MOM ON THE LINE?
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME, ARE YOU?
>> NO!
THE IDEA OF BLOOD VERSUS WATER,
IT'S HARD TRYING TO SELL MYSELF
WITHOUT FLOWING MY LOVED ONE
UNDER THE BUS.
AND THAT'S KIND OF THE ISSUE I'M
FACED WITH.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW HOW TO SAY,
"KEEP ME INSTEAD OF HER."
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GUYS READY TOO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
VYTAS.
I'LL TAKE THE NECKLACE BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
TODAY YOU'RE GOING TO
PARTICIPATE IN A "SURVIVOR"
CLASSIC.
THIS GOES BACK TO SEASON ONE.
GERVASE WAS A PART OF IT.
IT IS A FOOD EATING COMPETITION
IN WHICH YOU WILL RACE TO GET
DOWN LOCAL DELICACIES.
YOU'LL COMPETE IN A SERIES OF
ELIMINATION ROUNDS.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE AT THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS, AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, TAKE A SPOT UP AT THE
TABLE.
WE HAVE OUR FIRST ROUND OF FIVE.
THREE WILL MOVE ON FROM THIS
ROUND.
GO AHEAD AND TAKE THE TOP OFF.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: THESE ARE MEAL WORMS.
THERE ARE 40 OF THEM.
THESE ARE EATEN OUT HERE ALL THE
TIME.
IN FACT, FISHERMEN ARE OUT, THEY
USE THESE.
IF THEY GET HUNGRY, THEY TAKE A
COUPLE FOR A SNACK.
NO BIG DEAL IN THIS PART OF THE
WORLD.
THE FIRST THREE TO GET ALL 40
DOWN AND SHOW ME AN EMPTY MOUTH
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
>> CRAP.
>> Jeff: GO!
GOTTA GET THEM DOWN AND SHOW ME
AN EMPTY MOUTH.
DON'T THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
JUST CHEW IT AND GET IT DOWN.
TYSON'S GOOD, STEP BACK.
OH, THEY CAME UP FROM VYTAS.
HE'S GOT TO PICK THOSE UP, AND
HE IS.
SEVERAL CAME OUT OF HIS MOUTH.
MONICA'S GOOD.
TAKE A STEP BACK.
ONE MORE.
VYTAS IS STILL IN IT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: LAURA STRUGGLING.
LAURA HAS NO SHOT RIGHT NOW.
KATIE'S IN IT.
INCREDIBLE, VYTAS MOVES ON.
>> AWWW FUDGE.
>> Jeff: AFTER SPITTING UP
MEAL WORMS AND PICKING THEM BACK
UP, VYTAS, TYSON, AND MONICA
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR NEXT
FIVE.
GOING TO BE EATING THE SAME
THING.
TAKE OFF THE TOP.
>> OH!
>> THEY'RE JUST LIKE GUMMY
WORMS, EXCEPT FOR GROCER.
>> TINA'S ARE ALREADY HOPPING
OUT.
THREE WILL MOVE ON.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
40 MEAL WORMS.
GERVASE JUMPING UP AND DOWN ONCE
AGAIN LIKE IN SEASON ONE.
CIERA ALREADY SPITTING THEM UP
IN THE SAND.
TINA STRUGGLING.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS GET THEM
DOWN.
>> DIG DEEP, GUYS.
DIG DEEP.
>> Jeff: CALEB SPITTING THEM
BACK UP.
CIERA HAS GIVEN UP.
THAT MEANS THREE OUT OF FOUR OF
YOU WILL MOVE ON.
TINA, IT'S LIKE THEY'RE BITING
HER.
>> YOU'VE GOT IT, MOM.
>> YOU'VE GOT IT HAYDEN.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN HAS IT!
HAYDEN MOVING ON!
WE'RE LOOKING FOR TWO MORE.
GERVASE STRUGGLING TO GET THEM
DOWN.
TINA STILL FIGHTING.
CALEB'S GETTING VERY CLOSE.
>> CALEB, COME ON, LET'S GO,
BUD.
>> Jeff: LOOK AT THAT,
GERVASE, MOVING ON!
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE SPOT.
>> ALL RIGHT, MOM, IT'S YOU.
TINA SPILLING HERS OUT.
>> CALEB, IT'S ALL YOURS, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: CALEB MOVED ON TO
JOIN HAYDEN AND GERVASE IN THE
NEXT ROUND.
ALL RIGHT, TWO PEOPLE FROM THIS
ROUND ARE MOVING ON.
LET'S REVEAL THE NEXT FOOD ITEM.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> Jeff: PIG INTESTINES.
EVERYBODY HAS THREE OUNCES.
>> HOW ARE THEY PREPARED?
>> Jeff: BEAUTIFULLY.
>> I CAN DO THIS.
COM, MONICA.
>> Jeff: HERE WOO GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GERVASE NOT MESSING AROUND.
TYSON NOT MESSING AROUND.
CALEB TAKING A BIG CHUNK.
>> KEEP IT DOWN, HAYDEN.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN HAS A BIG
CHUNK.
DOES NOT WANT TO SPIT IT UP.
THEN HE HAS TO PICK IT UP.
>> Jeff: TYSON, COULDN'T HOLD
IT DOWN.
SPITS UP A LOT.
BACK ON HIS PLATE.
IT WILL BE EASY TO GET AND PUT
BACK DOWN.
( GAGGING ).
>> OH, GOD!
>> Jeff: IT IS NOT EASY TO GET
TO THE END OF "SURVIVOR."
IT IS NOT EASY TO GET A SHOT AT
A MILLION DOLLARS.
YOU'RE EARNING IT RIGHT NOW.
GERVASE SURPRISING EVERYBODY.
HE COULD BARELY DO THIS THE
FIRST TIME.
HERE HE IS STILL ALIVE.
VYTAS MAKING A LOT OF PROGRESS.
AFTER HIS BROTHER IS VOTED OFF
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL, HE'S
GOT TO BE WORRIED HE IS NEXT.
>> WAY TO GO, MONICA.
>> Jeff: MONCARC THE ONLY
WOMAN IN THE CHALLENGE, AND
BEING VERY CLOSE FOR BEING THE
OWN ONE MOVING ON.
>> THIS ONE FOR THE KIDS.
>> Jeff: FOR THE KIDS!
CALEB HOLDING BACK VOMIT.
>> OH, GOD!
>> Jeff: MONICA IS ONE BITE
AWAY FROM MOVING ON.
MONICA MOVES ON.
( APPLAUSE )
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE SPOT.
>> GET IT, GERVASE, COME ON.
>> Jeff: VYTAS HAS HIS LAST
BITE IN HIS MOUTH.
GERVASE DOWN TO HIS LAST BITE.
IT'S GOING TO BE CLOSE.
>> THAT A WAY, GERVASE, FINISH
IT.
>> Jeff: KEEP IT DOWN, VYTAS.
FIGHT IT, JUST FIGHT IT.
>> LAST BITE, YOU GOT IT.
COME ON, GERVASE.
>> Jeff: GERVASE, HAS IT!
MONICA AND GERVASE MOVING ON TO
THE FINAL!
CALEB, HAYDEN, TYSON, VYTAS, NO
SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
>> GOOD TRY, THOUGH, V.
>> Jeff: AND WE ARE DOWN TO
TWO.
GERVASE AND MONICA.
MONICA'S NEVER COMPETED IN THIS
BEFORE.
GERVASE HAS.
GERVASE, YOU FIND YOURSELF IN A
FOOD CHALLENGE.
HARKENING BACK TO THE VERY FIRST
SEASON IN WHICH THE ONE FOOD
ITEM YOU COULDN'T GET DOWN WAS A
GRUB.
NOW HERE ARE YOU 13 YEARS LATER,
IN THE FINAL, WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT LAST FOOD ITEM IS?
>> OH, NO.
>> Jeff: PULL IT OPEN.
REVEAL.
>> CAN'T DO THAT!
>> Jeff: YOU EACH HAVE TWO
DRUBS.
THEY WEIGH THE SAME IN COMBINED
WEIGHT.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS GET THEM
DOWN.
THERE IS NOWHERE TO HIDE.
ONLY ONE PERSON MOVES ON.
>> GERVASE, COME ON!
>>
>> Jeff: TWO GRUBZ.
SEASON ONE.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T DO THIS.
>> GOTTA GO FOR IT.
>> GOTTA.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO.
THIS IS IT, FOR IMMUNITY.
>> GOLLY.
>> Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> COME ON GERVASE.
>> Jeff: COME ON, GERVASE!
CHANGE HISTORY RIGHT HERE!
>> GET IT, GERVASE, COME ON.
>> Jeff: FIGHT THROUGH IT,
CULPEPPER.
KEEP IT DOWN!
MONICA HAS THE FIRST ONE DOWN.
MONICA WORKING ON HER SECOND.
GERVASE PUT BOTH OF THEM IN AT
ONCE.
>> GERVASE, YOU GOT IT.
TWO DIFFERENT STORIES.
FOR GERVASE A SHOT AT
REDEMPTION, FOR MONICA IT WOULD
BE HER FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: MONICA HAS IT!
MONICA WINS IMMUNITY!
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> I'M SO HAPPY.
GERVASE, I LOVE YOU, AND I'M
SORRY, BUT THIS HAS BEEN... OF
MINE FOR A LONG TIME.
THANKS FOR HELPING ME.
>> GOOD TRY, JERV.
>> Jeff: MONICA WINS IMMUNITY.
SAFE TONIGHT AT THE VOTE.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, 22 DAYS
INTO THIS GAME, SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT, SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
IT WON'T BE YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
( APPLAUSE )
GIRLS ARE DOING KATIE.
TONIGHT, THE PLAN IS FOUR VOTES
VISE' WAY, THREE VOTES KATIE'S
WAY.
AS OF RIGHT NOW, WE DON'T KNOW
IF ANYBODY HAS FOUND THE HIDDEN
MILE.
VYTAS MAY HAVE IT.
KATIE MAY HAVE IT.
TINA MAY HAVE IT.
>> I WASN'T THE ONE WHO CAME UP
WITH THE IDEA TO SPLIT THE
VOTES.
LAURA M. WAS LIKE, "IF THERE'S
AN IDOL OUT THERE WE NEED TO
SPLIT THE VOTES."
IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS DO I
TELL THEM I HAVE THE IDOL SO WE
DON'T WORRY ABOUT SPLITTING
VOTES OR IS THAT GOING TO MAKE
ME TOO BIG OF A TARGET?
I DON'T WANT TO TELL PEOPLE I
HAVE THE IDOL SO I HAVE TO JUST
ROLL WITH IT.
HE'S COMING UP THE BEACH RIGHT
NOW.
>> HOW WAS YOUR SHOWER.
>> HOW WAS THE TALK?
>> GREAT.
>> WHICH ONE OF US IS NEXT?
>> ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> GOING INTO THAT CHALLENGE, I
KNEW I NEEDED TO WIN IMMUNITY TO
ENSURE MY STAY.
AND I LOST IT.
SO RIGHT NOW, I'VE GOT PLENTY OF
WORK TO DO IF I WANT TO BE ABLE
TO STAY AROUND HERE JUST ANOTHER
DAY OR TWO.
WELL AT LEAST GIVE IT TO ME
STRAIGHT.
AM I GOING HOME TONIGHT?
YOU OWE ME THAT.
>> I'M GOING TO SHOOT STRAIGHT
WITH YOU 100%.
IT'S GOING TO BE YOU OR KATIE.
>> WE SPLIT FOR THE IDOL.
>> THIS IS THE WAY THE VOTE IS
GOING TO BE.
>> SO THERE ARE SEVEN.
SO IT'S GOT TO BE 4-3.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO HOPEFULLY, FOUR WILL GO TO
KATIE.
JUST GIVE ME ONE MORE, MAN.
>> I CAN'T.
>> IT'S A LITTLE LOW TO BEG FOR
MY POSITION ON THE TRIBE BUT I
REALLY HAVE NO OTHER PLAY.
JUST ANOTHER TWO DAYS ONN THIS
GAME COULD LEAD TO ANOTHER 12
DAYS IN THIS GAME, COULD LEAD TO
$1 MILLION.
IT'S SCRATCHING AND CLAWING TO
GET THROUGH TONIGHT'S TRIBAL.
AT THIS POINT, I'LL PUT KATIE'S
NAME DOWN IF IT GETS ME FURTHER.
I THINK IN THE END IT'S JUST
ABOUT NOT TURNING ON EACH OTHER.
I'M NOT TURNING OW GIRLS.
>> WELL, THAT'S OBVIOUS, BUT
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> I'M IN A VERY TIGHT JAM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ALLIANCES
PEOPLE HAVE RIGHT NOW.
MY MOM TOLD ME THAT I HAVE TO DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME.
SO I NEED TO FIGURE OUT A
DIFFERENT GAME POLICEMAN PLAN.
WHETHER THAT INCLUDES JUST ME OR
MY AND MY MOTHER.
>> I'M GETTING NERVOUS.
SEVEN US MADE A PACT THAT WE
WILL SPLIT THE VOTE BETWEEN
VYTAS AND KATIE.
SO THAT'S WHAT THE PLAN WAS.
HOWEVER, I'M NOT REALLY QUITE
SURE WHAT'S HAPPENING OR WHO IS
SAYING WHAT OR WHO'S DRIVING THE
BOAT.
BUT WHY THE SUDDEN SCRAMBLE?
IT MAKES ME FEEL VERY
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE WAS IT ME
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
SO THERE'S THIS MAD SCRAMBLE.
>> YOU WON.
>> THE BOYS ARE VOTING VYTAS.
>> AND WE'RE ALL WRITING KATIE.
>> ALL RIGHT, KATIE.
>> THAT'S GOOD BECAUSE I'M
LAYING HERE THINKING THERE'S A
WHOLE LOT OF SCRAMBLING GOING
ON.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN ME TONIGHT.
>> MONICA'S ASKING WHY EVERYBODY
IS SCRAMBLING AROUND?
WHY THE DOES SHE CARE?
SHE HAS THE NECKLACE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME.
THAT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU HOW
PARNOTIFIED A PERSON MONICA IS.
>> I KNOW THERE'S SEVEN YOU
GUYS.
YOU GOTTA SPLIT FOUR TO THREE
SOME WAY.
SPLIT THREE ON ME, PLEASE.
>> MEAN, THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
DOING.
>> BUT I JUST KIND OF ADD A
LITTLE SALT IN THE WOUND TO GO
RIGHT AFTER ARAS LIKE THAT.
>> AND THERE'S ALSO ONE LESS
PAIR OUT IF I STAY.
AS EVIDENCED BY LAST TRIBAL, YOU
KNOW, PAIRS ARE DANGEROUS.
>> ALL VALID POINTS.
>> AND I'LL PROMISE YOU THIS, IF
YOU KEEP ME AROUND ANOTHER ONE,
I'M MUCH MORE OPEN TO GIVING YOU
MY JURY VOTE AT THE END.
AT THIS POINT, THAT'S ALL I HAVE
LEFT.
>> VYTAS MADE SOME VALID POINTS
BUT THE MAIN CONCERN FOR ME
RIGHT NOW IS IF THE GIRLS WISE
UP, THEY COULD PERHAPS FORM AN
ALL-GIRL ALLIANCE, SENDING A
GIRL HOME WOULD KEEP VYTAS HERE
AND STILL KEEP THE GUYS IN THE
STRONG MAJORITY.
SO MY LIST OPT MALE RIGHT NOW
WOULD BE TO HAVE KATIE GO NEXT.
>> SINCE KATIE IS PLAYING HARDER
RIGHT NOW, WE SHOULD SEND HER.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> BUT IF WE'RE SOLID IT DOESN'T
MATTER WHAT ORDER WE DO IT IN.
>> RIGHT, BUT WE SHOULD DECIDE
RIGHT NOW.
THEN YOU CAN LET YOUR MOM KNOW.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I'LL DO WHATEVER.
>> THIS IS WHEN IT GETS
DANGEROUS FOR SOMEONE LIKE ME,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO COME OFF
AS THE KINGPIN OR THE DECISION
MAKER.
I WANT EVERYONE TO FEEL THEIR
INPUT IS WHAT MATTER MATTERS ANT
JUST MINE.
SO RIGHT NOW, I HAVE TO BE VERY
CAREFUL ABOUT THIS VOTE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: TINA, AFTER YOU GET
BACK TO CAMP AFTER THE LAST
TRIBAL, ARAS HAS BEEN
BLINDSIDED, WHAT WENT DOWN?
>> WELL, JEFF, IT WAS ONE OF
THOSE SITUATIONS WHERE I SHOULD
HAVE JUST KEPT MY BIG MOUTH
SHUT.
BUT I JUST COME OUT CUSSING
MONICA.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, IT WAS YOUR
BROTHER THEY TOOK OUT.
>> I WAS REALLY HAPPY TINA SAID
WHAT SHE DID.
I WAS FEELING IT.
YOU VOTED OUT MY BROTHER.
LIKE, I'M GOING TO ( BLEEP ) YOU
UP, MAN.
HOW DARE YOU VOTE OUT MY LITTLE
BROTHER.
I'M MY BROTHER'S KEEPER, AND IF
YOU DO THAT IN THIS GAME, I'LL
DO THE BEST TO GET YOU BACK.
I COULDN'T SAY THAT THEN, I'M
STILL STILL IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff:YOU JUST SAID IT.
>> I'M SAYING THAT'S A NATURAL
FEELING.
EVERYBODY HAS IT.
I WANTED THE FEELING TO COME OUT
FIRST, HEY, I GET IT.
I TOTALLY GET IT.
>> Jeff: GERVASE, YOU CAN
RELATE A LITTLE TO VYTAS?
>> OF COURSE, I UNDERSTAND HIS
ANGER, HIS RESENTMENT, ALL HIS
EMOTIONAL FEELINGS TOWARDS VYTAS
BEING VOTED OUT.
WHEN MARISSA GOT THROWN OUT, I
SAID I'M GOING TO WIN EVERY
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
I UNDERSTAND YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
>> I KNOW IT'S A GAME ABOUT
BETRAYAL.
THEY'RE SAYING ARAS HAD ALL OF
THESE ALLIANCES.
HE HAD A COUPLE AND PEOPLE
INTIMIDATED BY ARAS OR MYSELF
BLEW A LITTLE BIT OF AIR INTO
THAT FIRE.
NUMBER LIKE MONICA, WHO IS
ALREADY SO PARANOID OUT HERE,
SHE FELL FOR IT RIGHT AWAY.
YOU TELL HER SHE'S A DOOR MAT,
AND YOU SAY, TELL ME I'M A WORD
MAT.
>> I GAVE YOU MY WORD.
AND THAT'S ALL I HAVE IS MY
INTEGRITY OUT HERE.
I THINK YOU FLOPPED ON MY
HUSBAND, AND MY HUSBAND IS GONE,
BUT I STUCK MY NECK OUT TO GET
THRU TO LIVE VICARIOUSLY THROUGH
YOU ALL.
>> YOU WERE GETTING FURTHER TOO.
THIS MONICA THE BENEVOLENT
THING.
WOO WH WE LEFT GALANG, IT WAS
I'M TRUSTING YOU AND YOU'RE
TRUSTING ME, AND YOU BROKE THAT
TRUST.
>> Jeff: KATIE, IS IT SAFE TO
ASSUME THAT IT'S YOU, YOUR MOM,
OR VYTAS TONIGHT?
>> YES.
ABSOLUTELY.
IT COULD BE ME TONIGHT.
AND IF NOT, THEN I'M GOING TO
LOOK FOR THE CRACKS.
AND HOPEFULLY, THERE'S SOMEONE
HERE THAT WILL MAKE A MOVE.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, WHAT DO YOU
SAY TO THESE GUYS?
WHAT'S YOUR CASE?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT IF THE GIRLS TRY TO MAKE A
MOVE, AND YOU DON'T HAVE A GUY
LEFT, AND THE GIRLS ARE GOING TO
HAVE THAT NUMBER.
I THINK THAT IF GITONIGHT, THE
WOMEN WOULD BEHOOVE THEMSELVESES
TO REALLY, AND I THINK TYSON AND
GERVASE HAVE THE MOST POWER IN
THEIR ALLIANCE RIGHT NOW.
AND THOSE SHOULD BE THE GUYS
THAT THESE GIRLS SHOULD GET OUT.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
LAURA, YOU'RE UP.
>> WHAT UP, BRAD?
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
HIDDEN MILEAND YOU WANT TO PLAY
TNOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, VYTAS.
KATIE.
THAI SUN.
VYTAS.
THAT'S THREE VOTES VYTAS, ONE
VOTE KATIE, ONE VOTE TYSON.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES VYTAS.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VERSUS WATER."
VISE VYTAS.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
VYTAS, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
WELL, KATIE AND TINA, THE BAD
NEWS FOR YOU TWO IS THAT IT'S
VERY CLEAR YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
THE BAD NEWS FOR EVERYBODY ELSE,
IT MEANS YOU HAVE NOTHING TO
LOSE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
DPNT.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> WENT TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND I
WAS TOLD TO VOTE KATIE, BUT WITH
THE PRESSURE THAT I HAD BEEN
GIVEN BY VYTAS, AND THE VITRIOL
ATTACK THAT I HAD BEEN GIVEN BY
HIM AT TRIBAL, I CHOSE TO WRITE
DOWN VYTAS.
I WROTE HIS NAME DOWN.
HEY, HAYDEN, WHEN I WROTE VYTAS,
I SAID, "WHAT UP, BRAD?"
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
>> MONICA AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
DECIDED TO SWITCH HER VOTE.
SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO VOTE FOR
KATIE, BUT SHE DECIDES TO VOTE
FOR VYTAS.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENED AND THAT
WAS THE REASON WHY TYSON GOT
VOTE OUT, I GOT VOTED OUT, OR
ANYBODY ELSE IN MY ALLIANCE, I
WOULD HAVE LOST IT.
IT'S SIMPLE-- DON'T ROCK THE
BOAT.
MOVES LIKE THAT MAKE ME SAY YOU
KNOW WHAT?
LET'S GET RID OF MONICA NEXT.
ONE MORE STRAW, AND THE CAMEL'S
BACK WILL BE BROKEN.
>> I DID NOT EXPECT TO SEE YOU
LAST NIGHT, MAN.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE THAT GOT US
OUT OF THE GAME, BRO, COME ON.
>> THERE WAS NO WAY I COULD HAVE
SEEN IT.
>> THERE WERE SIGNS.
>> I THINK ARAS IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR GETTING ME HERE BECAUSE HE
SAID HE WAS GOOD.
I MEAN, I'M NOT GOING TO BRING
ANYBODY INTO AN ALLIANCE WITH MY
BROTHER AND SAY WE'RE 100% IF
WE'RE NOT 100%.
HE MADE THAT MISTAKE.
AND NOW I'M HERE GUILT BY
ASSOCIATION.
>> I'M STILL IN THIS GAME, BRO.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU KNOW THAT.
>> IT'S DIFFERENT, WE'RE NOT
ACTUALLY IN THE GAME.
>> WE'RE IN THE GAME.
>> IT'S PURGATORY.
>> IT'S NOT PURGATORY.
I'M IN THE GAME.
IF I WASN'T IN THE GAME, I WOULD
BE EATING A CHEESEBURGER RIGHT
NOW.
I'M NOT EATING A CHEESEBURGER SO
I'M IN THE GAME.
I'M GOING TO COME BACK AND WIN
THE GAME OR I WON'T.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> MY BROTHER HAS A VERY
NEGATIVE ENERGY AND I HAVE A
MUCH MORE POSITIVE ENERGY.
I LOVE HIM NO MATTER WHAT, BUT
BEST THINGS DON'T COME WHEN
YOU'RE PESSIMISTIC.
THEY COME WHEN YOU'RE OPEN AND
YOU'RE LIGHT.
>> THAT WILL BE GREAT.
IF YOU GET OUT OF REDEMPTION, I
WOULD BE JUST AS HAPPY AS IF I
GOT OUT OF REDEMPTION.
>> I CAN'T SAY THE SAME FOR YOU.
I'M SORRY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
MONICA, TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
BALANCE THE SWORD ON A CHEELD.
WITH THE OTHER HAND, YOU WILL
STACK COINS ON THE HANDLE.
WHEN THE STACK BECOMES TOO HIGH,
IT WILL BECOME HARD TO BALANCE.
THE COINS WILL FALL.
AND WHEN THE COINS FALL, YOU'RE
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE AT THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR SWORD.
PLACE IT ON THE SHIELD.
FIRST COIN YOU'RE GOING TO PLACE
IS A SMALL COIN.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO ADD A MEDIUM
COIN TO THAT.
GOING TO ADD ANOTHER SMALL COIN.
WE'RE GOING TO ADD A LARGE COIN.
BIGGEST ONE IN YOUR PILE.
YOU'VE NOT USED IT YET.
CIERA, LEFT HAND ALREADY SHAKING
AND WE'RE JUST STARTING.
GOING TO ADD ANOTHER SMALL.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, MONICA DROPS
HER COIN.
MONICA IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: CIERA DROPS HER COIN.
SHE IS OUT.
>> CRAZY.
>> Jeff: YOU CANNOT LOSE YOUR
FOCUS IN THIS CHALLENGE.
IF YOU DRIFT A LITTLE, AND THAT
STACK FALLS YOU COULD BE GOING
HOME TONIGHT.
ADD A MEDIUM COIN TO YOUR STACK
NOW.
COIN DROPPED ON TINA.
TINA IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
TAKE A STEP BACK.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO SIX.
>> GOOD JOB, KATIE.
>> Jeff: AND WITH THAT,
GERVASE DROPS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
HIS SHOT AT IMMUNITY IS OVER.
LAURA DROPS HER COINS.
SHE IS OUT.
EVERYBODY ELSE SURVIVES THIS
ROUND, AND WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
YOU'RE GOING TO ADD A SMALL
COIN.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
STARTING TO GET DICEY NOW.
STACKS A! STARTING TO GROW,
WIND PICKING UP A LITTLE.
GOING TO ADD ANOTHER SMALL COIN.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
FIND ONE YOU LIKE.
AND PLACE IT.
CALEB IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO THREE.
HAYDEN, KATIE, AND TYSON.
LIKE STATUES OUT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO ADD
ANOTHER MEDIUM COIN.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
RELEASE.
>> GOOD JOB, SWEETIE.
THATTA GIRL.
>> Jeff: WIND PICKING UP NOW
.
GOING TO ADD A LARGE TO YOUR
STACK.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO, THREE,
TWO, ONE.
TYSON DROPS, HAYDEN DROPS.
JUST LIKE THAT, KATIE WINS
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY, IS SAFE
TONIGHT AT THE VOTE.
EVERYBODY ELSE VULNERABLE AT
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
KATIE, COME ON OVER.
NICE JOB.
>> THANK YOU.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> IT NEVER LOOKED SO GOOD ON
YOU, HONEY.
>> WORK IT!
>> Jeff: KATIE, SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AFTER 24 DAYS, ONE OF YOU WILL
BE VOTED OUT OF THIS TRIBE, SENT
TO REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHERE YOU
WILL HAVE TO FIGHT TO GET BACK
IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
T'S MY GIRL!
>> WINNING THE IMMUNITY FEELS
LIKE WINNING THE LOTTERY.
BUT RIGHT NOW, WE DON'T HAVE AN
ALLIANCE.
IT'S JUST ME AND MY MOM FLAUL,
AWESOME.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> AWESOME.
>> WELL, I'VE GOT FIVE HOURS TO
FIND THAT IDOL.
THE REST OF THE DAY, THAT'S WHAT
I'M DOING.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I DON'T CARE IF THEY KNOW
IT.
>> THERE SHE GOES.
>> TINA JUST TOOK OFF THAT WAY.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'RE ALL GOING TO FOLLOW
TINA, EVERYBODY.
>> I DON'T EVEN HAVE ANY CLUES
TO WHERE THE IDOLS ARE, EXCEPT
KATIE SAID THAT IT WAS BETWEEN
SALT WATER AND FRESH WATER.
IT'S LIKE FINDING A NEED NEL A
HAYSTACK.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE'S UP THIS
HIGH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHY WOULD HAVE HAD TO RUN.
>> WE HEAD OUT, AND WE LOSE HER.
WE LOST HER ON THE WATERFALL
TRAIL.
I'M THINKING, WHAT THE HECK.
SHE DID GET THE SLIP ON US.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD SPLIT UP?
>> WANT TO DO THAT?
OKAY, DO IT.
THE IDEA WAS PEOPLE WOULD FOLLOW
TINA AROUND IN CASE SHE FIND THE
IDOL.
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
I GO TO EVERYBODY AND SAY I HAVE
THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
WE CAN ALL TAKE NAPS.
BUT THEN I BECOME A TARGET.
TODAY, WE HAVE TO BABY SIT TINA
ALL THE TIME.
SHE LOOKED IN THE RIGHT SPOT BUT
IT WAS GONE BECAUSE I MOVED IT
TO A SAFE PLACE.
>> ARE WE READY TO GO BACK?
>> WE ARE.
>> OKAY!
READY TO GO BACK AND EAT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> OR YOU CAN STAY.
WE DON'T CARE.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'LL STAY WITH YOU.
>> HOW'S IT GOING?
>> GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> GOOD.
>> I'M DEFINITELY IN A MEXICAN
STANDOFF, AND I'VE GOT TO FIND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THEY DON'T KNOW IF I HAVE IT OR
NOT, AND IF I START SEARCHING
FOR TTHEN THEY'RE GOING TO KNOW
I DON'T HAVE IT.
SO I'M JUST GOING TO STAY HERE
FOR A WHILE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG.
.>> SHE FIND THE IDOL, WHAT?
>> SPLIT VOTES BETWEEN-- IF SHE
FINDS THE IDOL, AND HER
DAUGHTER'S GOT IMMUNITY.
>> I'M NOT SURE WHOSE HAPPENING.
WE'LL SPLIT VOTES.
BETWEEN WHO?
SOMEBODY HAS GOT TO GO HOME.
THE QUESTION IS COULD IT BE ME.
>> THEY'RE NOT GOING FIND IDOL.
WE'LL WATCH THEM.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE'RE STICKING TO
THEM.
>> TONIGHT, IT'S MORE
COMPLICATED THAN I THOUGHT IT
WAS GOING TO BE.
THE THING IS, IS WE CAN'T SPLIT
THE VOTES.
BECAUSE THEN MONICA FEELS LIKE
SHE'S ON BOTTOM.
AND SHE'S A REAL WILD CARD, THAT
GIRL.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT SHE'S GOING
TO DO, AND THAT'S WHAT MAKES HER
DANGEROUS.
>> MONICA HAS SHOWN TO US THAT
SHE'S GETTING SUPER PARANOID,
WHICH SHE HAS A REASON TO BE
PARANOID.
>> AS LONG AS WE STICKS WITH THE
DAMN PLAN AND STOPS GOING
RENEGADE.
>> KNOW.
>> WHAT DID YOU WRITE VYTAS FOR.
THE PLAN WAS NOT TO WRITE
VYTAS'
NAME DOWN.
LOOSE CANNONS WILL ALWAYS SHOOT
OFF.
AND WHEN THEY DO, NINE TIMES OUT
OF 10 THEY WILL SINK SOMETHING
YOU'RE RIDING ON.
I WOULDN'T MIND VOTING MONICA
OUT.
>> ON THE OFF CHANCE, TINA DID
FIND THE IDOL, WE ALL JUST
MONICA.
>> WE CAN'T HAVE PEOPLE GOING
RENEGADE.
YOU CAN'T HAVE THAT HAPPEN.
>> MONICA IS ON THE OUTS BECAUSE
WE CAN'T TRUST HER.
EVEN IF TINA DOES NOT HAVE THE
IDOL, WE MIGHT HAVE TO CUT OUR
DISPIEZ SAY, SORRY, MONICA.
WE HAVE TO CUT YOU LOOSE.
>> MAYBE IT IS MONICA.
MAYBE IT'S GOOD TO GO NEXT.
>> Jeff: OKAY, SO AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, THERE WAS A VERY
CLEAR ALLIANCE OF SEVEN.
VYTAS WAS VOTED OUT.
SO UNLESS SOMETHINGS THAT
CHANGED THAT WOULD LEAVE TINA
AND KATE NETROUBLE.
KATIE WINS IMMUNITY TODAY, AND
PUTS IT ALL OW, TINA.
>> OH, YEAH.
NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT.
>> Jeff: SO WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> WELL, I ALL I COULD DO WAS
TRY TO FIND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL BUT WHAT WAS SO HYSTERICAL
IS I HAD BABY SITTERS ALL DAY.
THEY WENT EVERYWHERE I WENT SO I
HAD TO PULL A FAST ONE AND GET
AWAY FROM THEM AND AND RUN HIDE
FOR A WHILE.
>> Jeff: DID YOU HAVE TIME
FREE OF YOUR CAPTORS?
>> TWICE TODAY.
>> Jeff: BOY, TEEN AYOU JUST
DROPPED THAT, TWO WORDS "TWICE
TODAY."
READ INTO THAT WHATEVER YOU
WANT.
TINA, THE OTHER AVENUE YOU HAVE
WITH SEVEN PEOPLE IS TO FIND A
CRACK.
>> YOU'RE EXACTLY RIGHT, BECAUSE
IT CANNOT BE ALL OF THESE
PEOPLE.
I'M SORRY.
AND, YOU KNOW, POOR MONICA,
GUESS WHAT?
YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: WOW.
MONICA, TINA'S SAYING, LADY,
YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
>> THAT'S FINE.
PEOPLE HAVE THEIR OPINIONS.
BUT I'M ALSO WORKING INSIDE THE
ALLIANCE OF SEVEN.
AND I'VE HAD RELATIONSHIPS WITH
PEOPLE FROM DAY ONE.
HOPEFULLY, THOSE RELATIONSHIPS
WILL PULL THROUGH, AND WE'LL SEE
WHERE WE STAND.
>> SO ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU
DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU'RE ON THE
BOTTOM?
>> UM, YOU KNOW-- WHETHER OR NOT
I'M ON THE BOTTOM, IT'S CLEAR
AND APPARENT THAT TYSON AND
GERVASE ARE TOGETHER.
THAT HAYDEN AND CALEB ARE
TOGETHER.
AND THAT BOTH SETS OF MOTHERS
AND DAUGHTERS ARE TOGETHER.
SO DO I SOMETIMES FEEL LIKE I'M
NUMBER SEVEN?
SURE.
>> Jeff: TINA, THERE'S YOUR
CRACK.
>> AND, JEFF, EVERY TRIBAL
COUNCIL, SHE'S THE LAST ONE TOLD
WHO TO VOTE FOR BECAUSE MONICA,
SHE JUST TALKS WAY TOO MUCH.
AND IT MAKES PEOPLE SCARED TO
DEATH.
>> Jeff: GERVASE, WHEN DOES
SOMEBODY TALKING TOO MUCH BECOME
A LIABILITY?
>> INSTANTANEOUSLY.
I DON'T LIKE WILD CARDS BECAUSE
THEY CAN RUIN EVERYTHING JUST
LIKE THAT.
SO I LIKE TO KNOW WHAT MY HAND
LOOKS LIKE ALL THE TIME.
>> Jeff: SO, MONICA, WHAT IF
THEY JUST GET RIFD YOU TONIGHT?
THEY CAN GET RID OF TINA
WHENEVER THEY WANT.
>> SURE, YOU ALWAYS HAVE THAT
LITTLE BIT OF DOUBT.
EVEN TODAY, EVERYBODY SAY, OKAY,
SO WE'RE GOING TO VOTE TINA
TONIGHT.
AND I SAID HAS ANYBODY THOUGHT
IF TINA HAS THE IDOL?
AND THE RESPONSE WAS, "WE'LL
SPLIT VOTES."
I SAID IF SHE PLAYS THE IDOL AND
ONE HAS THE NECKLACE, WHO ARE WE
SPLITTING VOTES WITH?
AND THEN IT WAS, "OH, YEAH,
YOU'RE RIGHT."
>> Jeff: DOES IT CONCERN YOU
THAT MAYBE YOU'RE THE BOTTOM?
>> IT COULD VERY WELL MEAN I'M
THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN WHAT,
SITUATION WOULD IT MAKE SENSE IF
YOU WERE THINKING OF SPLITTING A
VOTE TO SAY, "YOU'RE RIGHT, WE
DON'T NEED TO."
IF TINA HAD THE IDOL, IT WOULD
BE ONE OF THE SEVEN OF YOU GOING
HOME IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE A BACKUP
PLAN.
>> OF COURSE.
WE RUN ALL THE SCENARIOS THROUGH
OUR MIEPPEDZ, AND IF SHE HAS THE
IDOL AND WE ALL VOTE FOR TINA,
IT IS ONE OF US GOING HOME, AS
YOU SAID.
ALL WE CAN DO IS THINK ABOUT IT,
SHOULD WE SPLIT THE VOTE AND
TAKE OUT THE BOTTOM?
MAYBE WE SHOULD.
>> AND THAT'S A REALLY SILLY
PLAN BECAUSE I'M EXTREMELY
TRUSTWORTHY.
AND I HAVE NOT OFFERED OR MADE
ANY PERSON A DEAL HERE AND ASKED
FOR ONE IN RETURN.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU COULD ASK
FOR A BETTER PLAYER.
>> Jeff: TINA, WHY QEEP YOU
AND GET RID OF MONICA?
>> WELL, ONE OF THE THINGS
STRATEGY-WISE I THINK THEY NEED
TO KNOW, TO LOSE MONICA TONIGHT
WOULD NOT BE THAT CRUCIAL AS FAR
AS NUMBERS ARE CONCERNED.
THEY WERE GOING TO PLAN A
BLINDSIDE ON SOMEBODY, BUT THEY
DID NOT WANT TO DO IT UNLESS
THEY ABSOLUTELY HAD TO.
AND THE ONLY WAY TO ENSURE A
BLINDSIDE TONIGHT WOULD BE IF I
FOUND THE IDOL.
SO MAYBE I HAVE.
MAYBE I HAVEN'T.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO SEE.
.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
LAURA, YOU'RE UP.
>> WHAT AN INSPIRATION.
THANKS FOR THE FUN.
STWR.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
>> JEFF.
I WISH I FOUND IT!
BUT I DIDN'T!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE
VOTES ARE READ, I DECISION IS
FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MONICA.
TINA.
TYSON.
ONE VOTE MONICA, ONE VOTE TINA,
ONE VOTE TYSON.
TWO VOTES TINA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES TINA.
TINA.
FOUR VOTES TINA.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VERSUS WATER.
OF THE TINA, THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S
ENOUGH PUP NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
>> I LOVE YOU, SWEETHEART.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> Jeff: TINA, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
>> SEE YOU ALL TOMORROW.
>> BYE, MOM.
>> Jeff: WELL, KATIE, THE BAD
NEWS SULOST YOUR MOM.
THE GOOD NEWS IS, THIS ALLIANCE
OF SEVEN IS NOT NEARLY AS TIGHT
AS THEY SEEM.
YOU'VE JUST GOT TO FIND YOUR WAY
IN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
IN BLOOD VERSUS WATER, THE ONLY
THING HARDER THAN VOTING SOMEONE
OUT IS VOTING OUT YOUR LOVED
ONE.
>> MY MOM IS EASY LET'S BIGGEST
TARGET RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M OKAY WITH MY MOM NOT
BEING IN THE GAME.
MY MOM NEEDS TO GO.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> HONEY, I'M HOME!
>> T.T.?
>> YES.
IT'S NOT-- YOU GET A SECOND
SHOT.
I'M GOING UP AGAINST TWO REALLY
TOUGH COMPETITORS, BUT EVERYBODY
HAS A CHANCE.
>> I'M JUST REAL HAPPY WE CAN
GIVE TINA A HUG, SET HER A
BLANKET BY THE FIRE, AND SEND
HER ON HER WAY TOMORROW.