>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR" -- FOR TYSON, LIFE IN
THE GAME WAS GOOD.
HE WAS IN A MAJORITY ALLIANCE
WITH GERVASE, MONICA AND CIERA
AND FOUND ANOTHER HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I THINK I'LL KEEP IT TO
MYSELF.
>> Jeff: BUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, HIS GAME STARTED
TO UNRAVEL.
>> CIERA, I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT
NOW, I'VE NEVER BETRAYED YOU AND
I'M PLANNING ON STAYING WITH
THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> SYRIA, YOU CAN COME WITH US,
YOU CAN DRAW ROCKS.
AND THAT'S A BIG MOVE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: CIERA FLIPPED ON HER
ALLIANCE.
MONICA, WE'RE TIED.
AND FOR THE SECOND TIME IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY THE GAME CAME
DOWN TO CHOOSING ROCKS.
AND REVEAL.
CIERA AND TYSON GOT LUCKY AND
KATIE WAS SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
KATIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN,
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
FIVE ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> KATIE?
>> HI!
>> OH!
>> BABY!
WERE.
>> WERE YOU SLEEPING?
>> NO, WE'VE BEEN WAITING UP.
>> KATIE'S HERE WITH ME SO OF
COURSE I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE HER.
BUT I'M NOT HAPPY THAT SHE'S OUT
OF THE GAME.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> WE HAD TO DRAW ROCKS TONIGHT.
>> UH-UH!
>> OH!
>> AND YOU DREW THE ROCK?
>> YEAH.
BUT IT WAS JUST BETWEEN THREE OF
US, THOUGH.
>> WHO DREW FIRST?
>> I DREW FIRST.
TONIGHT WAS MY SHOT TO KNOCK
TYSON OFF OF HIS THRONE AND I
COULD HAVE GONE FARTHERRER IN
THE GAME IF THINGS WENT MY WAY
BUT I HAD THE WHITE ROCK.
SO I WAS ROCKED OUT.
DO YOU THINK I SHOULD HAVE JUST
GONE WITH HAYDEN TONIGHT.
>> NO.
YOU HAD NOTHING TO LOSE.
I THINK IT'S GREAT THAT THEY ARE
WILLING TO DRAW ROCKS.
KUDOS TO THEM.
BUT THIS WILL PROBABLY BE THE
TOUGHEST REDEMPTION ARENA
BECAUSE KATIE AND I BOTH CAN'T
GO BACK INTO THE GAME.
IT'S GOT TO BE ONE OF US.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD BOTH TRY
OUR HARDEST.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE STILL MY
DAUGHTER.
IT'S HARD TO HAVE BEEN AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND NOW FOR NINE
DAYS AND YOU HOPE TO GET BACK IN
THE GAME AND TO FINISH WHAT YOU
STARTED BUT IT'S MY DAUGHTER AND
THAT TAKES PRECEDENCE ABOVE ALL
THINGS.
EVEN A MILLION DOLLARS.
I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU, KATIE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WOW!
CRAZY PLAY, GUYS.
>> CIERA, I OWE YOU A HUG.
>> YOU GUYS KNOW I LOVE
EVERYONE, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, NO, THAT WAS A GREAT
PLAY.
I WAS EXCITED TO BE PART OF IT.
IF I WERE KATIE I WOULDN'T
EXCITED TO BE PART OF IT BUT --
>> GREAT JOB.
>> CRAZY!
GREAT JOB.
>> MONICA, I LOVE YOU.
I HAD TO FIGHT HARD THROUGH
EVERYTHING.
I KNEW YOU WAS GOING HOME SO --
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT WAS
INSANE!
I'M LITERALLY -- I'M FIGHTING
FOR MY LIFE IN THE GAME.
AND THEN THE VERY NEXT MOMENT
WE'RE DRAWING ROCKS AND I
REALIZE THIS WORKED!
LIKE, WHAT?
I'M SAFE!
BEST-CASE SCENARIO WOULD HAVE
BEEN TYSON DREW THE WHITE ROCK
AND WENT HOME.
THAT WOULD HAVE FLIPPED THE
SCRIPT.
FLIPPED IT.
BUT ONE THING THAT'S NOT GOING
TO CHANGE IS I'M GOING TO BE
WITH CIERA ALL THE WAY TO THE
END.
YOU GUYS WOULD HAVE DONE THE
SAME THING.
TRY, TRY, TRY.
>> RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY YOU DON'T TELL AN
INSANE PERSON THEY'RE NEXT TO
GO-- GERVASE.
>> YOU SAYING I'M INSANE?
>> THE LAST THREE DAYS PROBABLY
PRETTY MUCH, YEAH.
YOU CAN'T EVER LET THE PERSON ON
THE BOTTOM KNOW THEY'RE GOING
HOME.
THAT'S "SURVIVOR" 101.
IT GIVES THEM A CHANCE TO BE
CRAZY.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE THEM HOPE.
YOU HAVE TO TELL THEM SOMEBODY
ELSE'S NAME.
BECAUSE THEN THE FIREWORKS
WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
>> THESE GUYS STICKING WITH ME,
I DON'T EVEN KNOW THAT WAS
ABOUT.
I PICKED UP MY BAG AND SAID
OKAY, I'M LEAVING AND YOU GUYS
-- I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT YOU GUYS
STUCK WITH ME!
I CANNOT BELIEVE IT.
>> THERE'S YOUR LINE IN THE
SAND.
>> BUT DON'T WORRY, I'VE ALREADY
GOT HER PULLING BACK OVER HERE.
I GOT HER.
NOW YOU'RE ALL ALONE AGAIN.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M ALWAYS IN THE
MIDDLE.
>> WE HAVE A GOOD ALLIANCE AND I
FEEL LIKE I'M IN A GOOD
POSITION.
BUT I'M CONCERNED THAT IF THEY
HAVE AN IDOL ONE OF US IS GOING
HOME.
>> MONICA, SHE'S CRUCIAL TO MY
GAME RIGHT NOW BUT SHE WILL NOT
STOP TALKING AND IT'S ANNOYING.
IT WAS LIKE STOP PLAYING THE
GAME, MONICA, YOU'RE PLAYING TOO
HARD RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M IN THIS WITH TYSON AND
GERVASE BUT I DON'T KNOW IF I
HAVE ANY RESPECT HERE.
I FELT LIKE WITHHOLDING THAT
CRUCIAL PIECE OF INFORMATION OF
HAVING AN IDOL THE WHOLE TIME,
IT HURT ME.
AND I'LL NEVER FORGET IT.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> SLEEP TIGHT, MONICA.
>> GOOD NIGHT, GUYS.
>> SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
>> SHE'S NOT GREAT AT
"SURVIVOR," BUT SHE'S REALLY
>> OH, YOU HERE IN THE HAMMOCK.
I WAS LIKE WHERE THE HECK IS
CIERA AT?
>> AFTER TRIBAL LAST NIGHT I
FEEL LIKE A HUGE WEIGHT JUST
LIFTED OFF MY SHOULDERS.
I KNEW I WAS NUMBER FOUR SO MY
MIND WENT YOU KNOW WHAT, CIERA?
THIS IS THE MOVE.
IF IT'S THE MOVE THAT SENDS YOU
HOME AT LEAST YOU WENT OUT
TRYING TO MAKE A MOVE VERSUS
RIDING TO THE FOUR AND NOT
SAYING YOU EVEN TRIED ANYTHING.
EVEN IT ENDED UP KATIE GOING
HOME WHICH SUCKED FOR US AT
LEAST WE MADE A MOVE.
BECAUSE THAT WAS OUR ONLY
OPPORTUNITY.
>> IF YOU DON'T GO DOWN FIGHTING
YOU'RE GOING TO BE PISSED.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGHT.
>> I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY IT DIDN'T
PAN OUT THE WAY I WANTED IT TO
PAN OUT.
KATIE WENT HOME.
WE'RE DOWN NUMBERS NOW 2-3.
BUT MY MOM BASED ON HER TRACK
RECORD WILL BE THE ONE COMING
BACK WHICH WOULD GIVE ME AND
HAYDEN THE NUMBERS.
AND THE FIRST TIME I WANT HER TO
COME OUT.
SO WE FIND THE IDOL, WE WAYNE
CHALLENGE.
IF WE DON'T WIN A CHALLENGE --
>> WE HAVE TO TRY TO DRIVE A
WEDGE BETWEEN THEM.
>> I WAS THINKING THAT SAME
THING.
HAYDEN AND I ARE BOUND AND
DETERMINED TO FIND A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, TO WIN A
CHALLENGE AND TO FIND THE CRACK
IN THE ALLIANCE BETWEEN GERVASE,
TYSON, AND MONICA.
WE'RE GOING TO GO ALL OUT.
BECAUSE THE GREAT THING ABOUT MY
POSITION RIGHT NOW, I HAVE
NOTHING TO LOSE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
TINA, LAURA AND KATIE, TINA'S
DAUGHTER VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
TINA, WHAT'S IT LIKE FOR YOU?
THIS IS YET ANOTHER LAYER OF
BLOOD VERSUS WATER.
YOU'RE OUT OF THE GAME, SO IS
YOUR DAUGHTER, ONLY ONE PERSON
CAN GET BACK IN THE GAME SO NOW
YOU'RE COMPETING AGAINST HER.
>> THIS IS BY FAR THE HARDEST
DAY.
>> Jeff: TINA, ARE YOU CAPABLE
OF GIVING 100% AGAINST THE YOUNG
WOMAN YOU GAVE BIRTH TO?
>> THAT'S A HARD ONE.
>> NO.
>> YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T CONCEIVED
IN MY MIND THE FINALITY OF IT SO
IT'S KIND OF LIKE WHAT I'VE
DECIDED IS I'M JUST GOING TO
PLAY TODAY AND I'LL MAKE THAT
DECISION IN THE MOMENT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL YOU'RE GOING TO
USE STICKS AND ROPE TO FASHION A
LONG POLE.
YOU'LL USE THAT POLE TO RETRIEVE
THREE KEYS.
THOSE KEYS OPEN THREE LOCKS.
THE FIRST TWO TO STEP THROUGH
THEIR DOOR LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER
DAY IN THIS GAME.
THE LAST PERSON IS OUT OF THIS
GAME FOR GOOD AND WILL BECOME
THE NEXT MEMBER OF THE JURY.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER OF THE
DUEL WILL DECIDE WHO GETS THE
CLUE TO THE LOCATION OF THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
TWO WILL LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER
DAY.
ONE WILL BE OUT OF THIS GAME FOR
GOOD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
>> KATIE, YOU'VE GOT TO DO YOUR
STICKS OVER AND UNDER AND ABOUT
A QUARTER TO A HALFWAY UP THE
POST.
>> OKAY.
THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: TINA IMMEDIATELY
BARKING OUTED A VICE.
IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
YOU HAVE SOME PIECES OF WOOD AND
SOME TWINE.
YOU HAVE TO FASHION A POLE LONG
ENOUGH TO GET IT THROUGHOUT TO
REACH THREE KEYS.
>> GOOD JOB, MOM.
>> Jeff: NOT ONLY DOES YOUR
STICK HAVE TO BE LONG ENOUGH, IT
HAS TO BE STRONG ENOUGH THAT YOU
CAN STICK IT OUT THERE AND IT
WON'T CRUMBLE.
LAURA HAS HER STICK PUT TOGETHER
ALREADY RIGHT OUT OF THE GATE.
SHE'S GOING FOR IT.
WILL IT BE LONG ENOUGH?
IT IS.
SHE HAS THE FIRST KEY, CAN SHE
GET IT BACK THROUGH THAT GATE?
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: YES, SHE DOES.
LAURA HAS HER FIRST CHAI AND
SHE'S IMMEDIATELY GOING FOR THE
SECOND.
KATIE HAS HER POLE TOGETHER.
SHE'S GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
TINA HAS HER POLE TOGETHER,
THERE ARE THREE KEYS TOTAL.
TINA A LITTLE SHORT.
SHE NEEDS MORE.
KATIE, IS IT LONG ENOUGH?
YES.
IS IT STRONG ENOUGH?
LAURA GOING FOR HER SECOND KEY.
LAURA HAS HER SECOND KEY.
KATIE HAS HER FIRST KEY.
KATIE HAS HER FIRST KEY THROUGH.
IT'S KATIE WITH ONE KEY.
LAURA NOW LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
TINA HAS NOTHING YET.
LAURA GOING FOR HER THIRD.
>> COME ON, GIRLFRIEND!
>> Jeff: SHE'S GOT IT THERE,
IT'S LONG ENOUGH.
IS IT STRONG ENOUGH TO HOOK IT?
IT IS.
CAN SHE GET IT BACK THROUGH
WITHOUT IT DROPPING?
SHE DOES!
LAURA HAS ALL THREE KEYS.
SHE'S GOT TO OPEN THE LOCKS AND
SHE WILL MOVE ON.
>> SHE'S A FREAK.
>> Jeff: LAURA HAS HER FIRST
LOCK UNDONE.
TINA GOING FOR HER FIRST.
SHE'S THERE, IT'S LONG ENOUGH.
SHE HAS IT HOOKED.
TINA HAS HER FIRST.
LAURA HAS HER SECOND LOCK
UNDONE.
ONE LEFT AND LAURA MOVES ON.
LAWYER A A HAS BEEN UNSTOPPABLE
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
LAURA WINS ANOTHER DUEL AND WILL
STAY ALIVE ONE MORE DAY ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IT IS NOW DOWN TO MOTHER AND
DAUGHTER LOOKING FOR THAT SECOND
SPOT.
THE QUESTION IS: WILL TINA FIGHT
HARD ENOUGH TO DEFEAT HER
DAUGHTER OR WILL SHE SACRIFICE
HERSELF FOR HER DAUGHTER IN
"BLOOD VS. WATER" MOTHER AND
DAUGHTER NECK IN NECK BOTH
LOOKING FOR TWO MORE RINGS.
TINA'S POLE BREAKS OPENS THE
DOOR FOR HER DAUGHTER KATIE.
SHE HAS THE SECOND RING HOOKED.
>> WALK BACKWARDS, WALK BACK.
>> LET'S GO KATIE.
>> Jeff: CAN SHE KEEP IT ON?
NO, IT DROPS IN THE SAND.
THAT COULD BE MORE DIFFICULT.
NOW SHE'S GOT TO GET IT OUT OF
THAT SAND WITH THE SAME LONG
STICK.
IT'S TOO FAR TO REACH OTHERWISE.
TINA GOING TO GIVE IT ANOTHER
GO.
>> GET LOWER.
>> Jeff: KATIE TRYING TO DIG
THAT OUT OF THE THE SAND.
VERY DIFFICULT TO GET IT OUT OF
THE SPOT.
TINA, IS IT LONG ENOUGH?
YES, SHE'S GOT THE KEY HOOKED.
TINA HAS HER SECOND RING.
CAN SHE GET IT BACK?
TINA HAS HER SECOND KEY!
TINA'S DOWN TO RUN RING LEFT.
>> COME ON, KATIE.
>> KATIE NOT PANICKING.
SHE'S UNDER IT.
CAN SHE HOOK IT?
NO, FALLS SHORT AGAIN.
TINA'S GOING FOR HER THIRD RING
IF SHE CAN JUST REACH IT.
SHE HAS IT HOOKED.
CAN SHE GET IT BACK?
THIS WILL PUT TO REST ANY NOTION
OF LETTER HER DAUGHTER WIN RIGHT
HERE.
GOT TO KEEP IT ON THAT STICK AND
GET IT THROUGH THE GATE.
IT'S SLIDING TOWARD THE EDGE.
TINA HAS HER THIRD KEY.
ALL SHE HAS TO DO NOW IS UNLOCK
THE THREE LOCKS AND SHE MOVES ON
AND KATIE WILL BE OUT OF THIS
GAME FOR GOOD.
>> KATIE, ARE YOU OKAY WITH
THIS?
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT, MOM.
>> Jeff: TINA HAS THE FIRST
LOCK UNDONE.
>> YOU SURE?
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> I LOVE YOU, HONEY.
>> Jeff: COMPLICATIONS OF
"BLOOD VS. WATER" PLAYING OUT
RIGHT HERE.
TINA HAS HER THIRD LOCK.
JUST PULL THAT CHAIN, YOU'RE
DONE.
>> GO, WALK THROUGH.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> Jeff: AND WITH MIXED
EMOTIONS TINA SURVIVES
REDEMPTION ISLAND JOINING LAURA.
>> DON'T CRY.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> I'M SORRY, HONEY.
>> DON'T BE SORRY.
YOU DID GREAT.
>> I'M PROUD OF YOU.
>> I'M PROUD OF YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: TINA, YOU LOVE THIS
GAME, YOU LOVE COMPETING.
YOU DO NOT LOVE BEATING YOUR
DAUGHTER.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> YOU KNOW, JEFF, THERE IS
SOMETHING ABOUT MY RELATIONSHIP
WITH KATIE BECAUSE I WAS ADOPTED
AND I DON'T HAVE THOSE
CONNECTIONS IN MY LIFE.
I -- IT WASN'T UNTIL I HAD HER
THAT I FELT MY FIRST CONNECTION
IN LIFE.
AND SO --
>> DON'T MAKE ME CRY.
>> Jeff: TOO LATE.
>> AND SO IT'S JUST A PURE
UNADULTERATED COMPLETE LOVE.
AND THAT'S ALL I CAN SAY.
I JUST LOVE HER.
>> Jeff: KATIE, CAN YOU
EMPATHIZE WITH WHAT SHE'S
FEELING?
>> YEAH, I COULD TELL RIGHT OFF
THE BAT WHEN I LOOKED AT HER
THAT THE FLOOD OF EMOTIONS CAME
IN.
BUT I'M SO INCREDIBLY PROUD OF
BOTH MYSELF AND MY MOTHER AND TO
BE ABLE TO EXPERIENCE THIS
TOGETHER IS THE BEST GIFT I
COULD HAVE ASKED FOR, REALLY.
>> Jeff: CAUGHT KATIE, AFTER
33 DAYS OUT HERE, YOUR RUN AT
THE MONEY AND THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR HAS COME TO AN END.
YOU CAN GRAB YOUR STUFF, TOSS
YOUR BUFF IN THE URN ON THE WAY
OUT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU.
EAT A HAMBURGER FOR ME, OKAY?
>> BYE, KATIE!
GREAT JOB, KATIE!
>> BY, JEFF, THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: SEE YOU, KATIE.
>> LOVE YOU, BABY.
>> LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> WAY TO GO, SWEETIE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAURA,
AFTER WINNING ANOTHER DUEL --
>> ANIMAL!
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN YOU DECIDE
WHO GETS THE CLUE TO THE
LOCATION OF THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
SHOULD YOU WALK IT TO YOUR
DAUGHTER?
>> CAN I WALK IT TO HER?
>> Jeff: ABSOLUTELY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> FIND THAT THING.
>> WIN THE CHALLENGE HAYDEN.
>> Jeff: TINA, LAURA, YOU GET
TO SEE YET ANOTHER DAY OUT HERE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
RED.E.REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AWAIT YOUR NEXT COMPETITOR AND
YOUR NEXT DUEL.
>> BY MOM, LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: GUYS, GRAB YOUR
STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
OUT ON A LIMB ON A TREE BACK
THERE.
>> REDEMPTION ISLAND WAS A
SUCCESS FOR MY MOM.
IT WAS GREAT TO WATCH HER WIN
AGAIN.
SO MY MOM WINS AND SHE GIVES ME
THE CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL WHICH IS NEEDED RIGHT NOW.
ME AND HAYDEN'S ONLY HOPE IN
THIS GAME RIGHT NOW IS ONE OF US
NEEDS TO WIN THE CHALLENGE AND
ONE OF US HAS TO FIND THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL BECAUSE THEN WE'RE
SAFE AND MONICA, TYSON AND
GERVASE HAVE TO VOTE AGAINST
EACH OTHER.
>> I I'M UP CLIMBING UP TREES
LIKE A MONKEY AND MONICA COMES
STROLLING UP BACK TO THE WELL TO
GET SOME WATER AND I'M THINKING,
GREAT, NOW EVERYBODY AND THEIR
BROTHER KNOWS THE IDOL IS OUT ON
A LIMB.
>> WHAT'S UP, HAYDEN.
>> OH, YOU KNOW.
HANGING AROUND.
>> HANGING AROUND?
CHECKING OUT THE TREES?
>> UH-HUH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S SO FRUSTRATING TO ME.
I'M DRIVING MYSELF CRAZY OUT
HERE, I REALLY AM.
BECAUSE I CAN WIN THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE ALL DAY LONG BUT IF I
DON'T FIND THE IDOL CIERA'S
GOING HOME.
I HAVEN'T FOUND IT YET, I'VE
BEEN ALL OVER THE (BLEEP)ING
TREE.
THERE'S ONE BIG TREE, THAT'S THE
OBVIOUS ONE AND I HAVE CLIMBED
IT.
BEEN ALL OVER IT.
THE IDOL IS NOT THERE.
SOMEBODY HAS IT ALREADY.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
TYSON MIGHT HAVE THE IDOL.
>> THEY'RE ALL STILL AGAINST US.
YOU HEARD TINA KATE HAYDEN WIN
THE CHALLENGE."
>> AND "CIERA FIND THE IDOL."
>> THIS GAME IS CRAZY AND
CHANGES ALL THE TIME AND AFTER
THAT LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL I KNOW
I HAVE TO WORK TO GET TO THAT
FINAL FOUR SPOT SO EVEN THOUGH
SHE'S A WILD CARD, I KNOW I'M
GOING TO NEED MONICA TO MAKE IT
TO THE END OF THIS GAME.
THAT MEANS I NEED TO DO
EVERYTHING IN MY POWER TO MAKE
SURE NOTHING MESSES UP THIS
THREE-PERSON ALLIANCE AND I NEED
TO DO EVERYTHING IN MY POWER TO
MAKE SURE US THREE ARE SITTING
IN THE FINAL.
SO 1-10, HOW MUCH DO YOU TRUST
ME?
>> 10.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU TRUST HAYDEN?
>> HAYDEN IS SCRAMBLING.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU TRUST CIERA?
>> 5.
>> (LAUGHS)
YOU'RE GENEROUS.
>> 5.
>> I WOULDN'T HAVE EVEN GIVEN
HER A FIVE.
YOU'RE GENEROUS.
HOW MUCH DO YOU TRUST TYSON.
>> HE'S IN MY ALLIANCE.
I TRUST HIM AT 10.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE SAID "I TRUST YOU AND
TYSON TO A 10.
" DEFINITELY WANT TO HEAR THAT.
THE TRUST THAT MONICA IS GIVING
OUT, YOU COULDN'T PAY FOR IT.
>> I TRUST YOU A 10 MYSELF.
>> SO I APPRECIATE YOU GUYS.
>> YOU'RE GOLDEN.
>> I APPRECIATE YOU GUYS SAVING
ME.
I KNOW YOU DID THAT.
YOU ALL COULD HAVE FLIPPED ON ME
BUT YOU ALL CHOSE ME.
I'M STILL HERE BECAUSE TYSON
DREW ROCKS.
I MEAN, THEY'RE BOTH MY GUYS.
I'VE TRIED TO PLAY VERY SELFLESS
OUT HERE.
AND THE ACT THAT THOSE TWO GUYS
DID WAS SELFLESS, TOO.
AND SO WHAT THEY DID LAST NIGHT
FOR ME, IT MEANT SOMETHING.
IT'S CALLED SCRUPLES.
>> TRUST ME, I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> I LIKE THESE GUYS AND I THINK
THEY GENUINELY LIKE ME AND I
FEEL LIKE I WILL HAVE A BOND
WITH THOSE TWO GUYS FOREVER.
I HAVE LOVED YOU FROM DAY ONE.
>> SAME-SAME.
>> BUT YOU'VE GOT TO BE ABLE TO
SEPARATE REAL LIFE AND THE GAME
OF "SURVIVOR."
SO I AM PLAYING THIS GAME FOR
MONICA, NOT TYSON AND GERVASE.
MONICA.
>> WE'VE GOT TO COME UP WITH A
PLAN.
>> I'LL PROBABLY TALK TO --
>>GERVASE IS NOT GOING TO FLIP.
>> NOT AT ALL.
OUR ONLY CHANCE IS MONICA.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO THROW THE
BOYS UNDER THE BUS?
>> UH-HUH.
>> DO IT.
HARD.
>> I WILL.
I'LL JUST GO TO TYSON AND --
I'LL SAY "YOU'RE DUMB, THEY'LL
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT THEM TO
DO."
>> TELL HER SHE'S ON A LEASH.
>> THE HAIL MARY PLAY IS TO TELL
MONICA TYSON AND GERVASE ARE
TALKING CRAP ABOUT HER AND SEE
IF WE CAN GET HER TO FLIP ON
OVER TO THE GOOD GUYS.
COME SEE THE LIGHT, MONICA.
WE'RE THE GOOD GUYS.
THE GOOD GUYS NEED TO WIN THIS.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES. FIRST,
GERVASE, I BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO DIVE INTO THE WATER AND
PUSH A BUOY ALONG A ROPE AND
THROUGH AN OBSTACLE.
ONCE YOU REACH THE SHORE, YOU'LL
UNTIE A BAG OF LETTER TILES AND
USE THEM TO SOLVE A CLASSIC
"SURVIVOR" PHRASE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOSERS, AFTER 35 DAYS, SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT, SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL
HAVE TO COMPETE AGAINST LAURA
TINA-- TWO W
COMPETITORS-- TO GET BACK IN
THISAME.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF TODAY'S
CHALLENGE WILL GET TO ORDER FROM
A "SURVIVOR" MEN YAW PREPARED A
ESPECIALLY FOR YOU AND HAVE THE
FOOD DELIVERED TO CAMP.
YOUR CHOICES OF ENTREE INCLUDE
STEAK, LOBSTER, PIZZA, BURGER,
REAL FOOD PROVIDING A REAL
ADVANTAGE OF THESE LAST FEW DAYS
WHEN FOOD IS VERY HARD TO COME
BY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
HAYDEN AND TYSON OUT QUICKLY.
MONICA RIGHT BEHIND.
GERVASE AND CIERA ARE BRINGING
UP THE REAR.
GERVASE IS EVEN BEATING CIERA
AND GERVASE IS NO STAR IN THE
WATER.
IT IS HAYDEN AND TYSON SIDE BY
SIDE.
MAN, THEY ARE CRUISING THROUGH
THIS.
MONICA TO HER PLATFORM.
GERVASE TO HIS PLATFORM.
TYSON BACK IN THE WATER.
CIERA FINALLY TO HER PLATFORM.
HAYDEN BACK IN THE WATER.
GERVASE TRYING TO WORK THROUGH
THIS.
MONICA TRYING TO WORK THROUGH
IT.
MONICA BACK IN THE WATER.
GERVASE RIGHT BEHIND MONICA.
TYSON IS FIRST BACK TO SHORE.
THERE'S HAYDEN.
START UNTYING YOUR LETTER TILES.
CIERA IS STILL STRUGGLING,
GIVING UP A LOT OF TIME AND A
BIG IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
MONICA'S BACK.
TYSON HAS HIS LETTER TILES.
HE'S STARTING ON THE PHRASE.
CIERA IS DEAD LAST IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
HAYDEN HAS HIS LETTER TILES.
MONICA HAS HER BAG.
GERVASE HAS HIS OUT.
THEY CAN START WORKING ON THEIR
PHRASE.
CIERA THE LAST ONE TO THE
PLATFORM TO START UNTYING HER
BAG OF LETTER TILES.
TYSON IS WORKING ON IT.
HAYDEN HAS ALREADY STARTED.
GERVASE IS IN ON IT.
MONICA IS WORKING ON IT.
YOU ARE FORMING AN EIGHT-WORD
PHRASE.
THERE WILL BE MANY WORDS YOU CAN
FORM THE TRICK IS FORMING THE
RIGHT WORDS.
CIERA HAS HER LETTER TILES.
SHE CAN START WORKING ON IT.
SHE IS WAY BEHIND RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS A COMMON "SURVIVOR"
PHRASE.
DOESN'T MEAN IT'S EASY.
BUT IF YOU ARE A FAN OF THIS
SHOW, YOU HAVE HEARD IT BEFORE.
MONICA HAS A COUPLE WORDS.
THE QUESTION IS, ARE THEY THE
RIGHT WORDS?
TYSON THINKS HE HAS SOMETHING.
YOUR BEST BET IS TO TRY LOTS OF
COMBINATIONS.
IF YOU GET STUCK ON ONE THREE OR
FOUR-LETTER WORD AND YOU DON'T
MOVE IT, YOU'RE FALLING BEHIND.
YOU'VE HEARD ME UTTER A PHRASE
VERY SIMILAR TO THIS THIS
SEASON.
GERVASE NOW RACING TO PUT
TOGETHER A FIFTH WORD.
IF HE'S RIGHT, HE'S ALMOST
THERE.
THERE ARE EIGHT WORDS IN THIS
PHRASE.
CIERA NOT GIVING UP.
SHE WAS LAST HERE BUT SHE'S IN
IT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE NOW CIRCLING THE
SAME WORDS.
THAT COULD BE A GOOD SIGN.
YOU HAVE HEARD THIS.
I HAVE SAID IT TO YOU.
CIERA THINKS SHE'S ON TO
SOMETHING.
GERVASE THINKS HE HAS SOMETHING.
MAYBE HE HAS AN IDEA THAT'S
RIGHT.
HE HAS SIX WORDS.
CIERA HAS SIX.
THEY ARE NECK IN NECK.
IF THEY'RE RIGHT.
CIERA TRYING DIFFERENT
COMBINATIONS FOR THESE LAST TWO
WORDS.
SHE'S MOVING VERY QUICKLY.
CIERA THINKS SHE HAS IT AND SHE
DOES!
YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE TO DIG
DEEP!
CIERA WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
>> I WON ONE!
>> YEAH, CIERA!
CIERA, COME ON OVER.
CIERA, SAFE AT TONIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IN ADDITION, YOU'VE WON REWARD.
BEFORE YOU DECIDE WHAT YOU WANT
TO HAVE DELIVERED TO CAMP,
CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO JOIN YOU
FOR LUNCH.
>> HAYDEN.
>> DIDN'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
HAYDEN ALL THE WAY.
HAYDEN, COME ON OVER.
>> NICE JOB!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THIS MENU
IS FOR YOU.
YOU CAN EACH PICK ONE ENTREE.
ALL RIGHT, THIS FOOD WILL BE
DELIVERED TO YOU AT CAMP.
IT IS YOURS ONLY.
NO SHARING WITH TYSON, MONICA
AND GERVASE.
TO THE BIGGER ISSUE, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
CIERA IS SAFE, NOT GOING HOME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, HAYDEN,
TYSON, MONICA, GERVASE, AFTER 35
DAYS, ONE OF YOU WILL BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS TRIBE, SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL
HAVE TO COMPETE FOR A SHOT BACK
IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> Jeff: CIERA!
>> GREAT JOB!
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
>> YES, I CAN BELIEVE IT!
>> OH, MY GOSH!
I JUST WON!
I JUST WON IMMUNITY AND IT IS
UNREAL.
THE FIRST THING THAT WENT
THROUGH MY MIND INSTEAD OF "I'M
SAFE" OR "INSTEAD OF I GET TO
EAT" IS "WHEN MY MOM HEARS THIS
SHE'S GOING TO BE SO PROUD OF
ME."
ALL OF YOU PEOPLE LOOKING AT ME
LIKE I MADE A STUPID DECISION
TRYING TO GO AGAINST ALL MIGHTY
TYSON, IN YOUR FACE BECAUSE I
JUST DID IT.
DON'T EVER COUNT ME OUT.
MY MOM IS POTENTIALLY COMING
BACK INTO THIS GAME THEN YOU
HAVE TWO TO WORRY ABOUT NOT JUST
ONE.
>> I'M PROUD OF YOU.
I REALLY AM.
>> THANK YOU.
I'M PROUD OF MYSELF.
I THINK THE FACT I CHOSE HAYDEN
ALSO SHOWS WE'RE NOT SCARED.
I'M NOT TRYING TO KISS TYSON'S
ASS AND IT'S THE BEST FEELING
EVER AND NOW THAT I KNOW WHAT IT
FEELS LIKE I'M GOING TO BE GOING
FOR THAT EVERY SINGLE TIME.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, I
NEEDED TO WIN TODAY AND WHAT DO
YOU KNOW?
I FREAKING LAY AN EGG.
SO I'VE GOT TO PULL A RABBIT OUT
OF MY HAT IF I'M GOING TO STICK
AROUND.
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS CIERA DID
WIN AND WE GOT TO CRUSH SOME
FOOD.
>> CHEERS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S ALMOST BETTER THAT ALL
THREE OF US DON'T GET TO EAT
TOGETHER.
>> THAT'S A NICE WAY TO LOOK AT
IT.
>> JUST STICK TO THE PLAN?
>> YUP.
>> HAYDEN?
>> IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO SEE
WHO THEY TARGET.
PROBABLY ME AGAIN.
>> THINK THEY'RE FREAKING OUT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> YEAH.
THEY'RE WORRIED.
>> UH-HUH.
>> SO TALK TO MONICA, TELL HER
TO VOTE GERVASE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> TELL HER THE TWO OF US ARE
GOING TO VOTE GERVASE BECAUSE WE
THINK TYSON HAS AN IDOL.
>> AND I'M GOING TO TELL HER
EVERYTHING ABOUT TYSON AND
GERVASE, EVERYTHING.
>> THROW THEM UNDER THE BUS.
>> UH-HUH.
I'M GOING ALL OUT WITH HER.
I'M NOT LEAVING ANYTHING OUT.
HAYDEN AND I HAVE NOT FOUND THE
IDOL SO RIGHT NOW OUR ONLY
CHOICE IS TO FIGURE OUT WHO IS
THE CRACK IN THE ALLIANCE
BETWEEN GERVASE, TYSON, AND
MONICA.
AND MONICA IS DEFINITELY THE
CRACK.
>> SO YOU'RE GOING TO TALK TO
MONICA?
>> YEAH.
SHE'S AN EMOTIONAL WRECK OUT
HERE RIGHT NOW SO IF I CAN PLAY
ON THAT AND IF I CAN THROW TYSON
AND GERVASE UNDER THE BUS MAYBE
SHE'D BE WILLING TO WORK WITH ME
AND HAYDEN.
SOMETHING I WANT TO TELL YOU--
HONEST.
>> OKAY.
>> IS THAT TYSON IS A VILLAIN IN
THIS GAME.
AND I KNOW YOU DON'T THINK SO
BECAUSE, LIKE, YOU'RE IN TIGHT
WITH HIM.
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT HE WAS TALKING MAD CRAP
ABOUT YOU.
AND SAYING THAT -- TONS OF
THINGS AND SAYING THAT YOU WERE
GOING TO BE AN EASY VOTE FOR HIM
TO BRING IN.
HE SAID YOU'RE WEAK.
HE SAID YOU'RE PARANOID.
AND HE SAID YOU'RE A PUPPY ON
HIS LEASH AND YOU'LL VOTE
HOWEVER.
HE'S LIKE "DON'T WORRY, MONICA'S
WITH ME, SHE'S MY PUPPY, SHE'LL
DO WHATEVER YOU TELL HER TO DO."
HE'LL TALK ALL NICE TO YOU AND
THEN HE'LL ROLL HIS EYES WHEN
YOU SAY SOMETHING.
RUDE, MEAN, HURTFUL THINGS.
>> STILL?
>> STILL.
HE WAS TELLING ME ALL OF THESE
THINGS AND I PROMISE YOU.
>> HOW WOULD YOU EXPLAIN, THEN,
TYSON GOING ALL THE TRY THE END
TO DRAW ROCKS?
>> TYSON DID THAT BECAUSE TYSON
KNEW IF TYSON -- IF TYSON WOULD
HAVE FLIPPED AND VOTED YOU OUT,
GUESS WHO WAS NEXT?
TYSON BECAUSE WE HAD THE
NUMBERS.
>> RIGHT.
>> THAT'S THE ONLY REASON HE DID
THAT.
SO JUST -- JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
COME ON, I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T
MEAN TO MAKE YOU CRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
IT'S A HARD GAME.
>> I'M GLAD TO KNOW THE
INFORMATION BUT DAMN!
IT HURT ME.
I MEAN, IT WAS LIKE A GUT PUNCH.
I CAME IN SAYING TO GET TO THE
END I MIGHT HAVE TO MISLEAD AND
MISDIRECT BUT I CAN GUERIN
(BLEEP) TEE YOU I WOULD NEVER
HURT SOMEONE AND THERE'S A BIG
DIFFERENCE.
SO GUESS WHAT?
IT'S NOW BECOME A ME GAME.
>> DO WHAT'S BEST FOR MONICA BUT
JUST KNOW IT.
AND IF YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING, VOTE GERVASE TONIGHT.
>> TONIGHT TYSON AND GERVASE,
THEY'RE GOING TO BE ON THE
DEFENSE FOR THE FIRST TIME AND
MONICA'S GOING TO BE ON THE
OFFENSE BECAUSE IF I AM THEIR
PUPPY DOG, THEY BETTER STAND
CORRECTED.
>> YOU THINK SHE'S OKAY DOWN
THERE?
>> LOOKS LIKE IN A MATTER OF
MOMENTS I AM THE SWING VOTE.
CIERA AND HAYDEN NEED ME TO GO
WITH THEM.
TYSON AND GERVASE NEED ME TO GO
IT'S UP TO MONICA.
>> IS MONICA GOOD WITH CIERA
WITH HER?
>> AND CIERA CAME UP SMILING
KIND OF.
>> YOU KNOW, I TRUST HER NOW AND
I HAVE NO DOUBT IN MY MIND SHE'S
NOT GOING TO SWAY.
>> YOU NEVER KNOW, YOU KNOW?
I'M GETTING NERVOUS, DUDE.
>> WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ARAS, VYTAS, CALEB AND KATIE.
>> STUNNER!
>> SHE LOOKS HOT.
>> OKAY, SO AT THE
LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, CIERA, YOU MADE A BIG
MOVE, YOUR SIDE LOST.
WAS IT STILL THAT DIVISION GOING
INTO TODAY'S CHALLENGE?
>> DEFINITELY.
I MEAN, ME AND HAYDEN KNEW THAT
IT WAS THEM THREE VERSUS TWO AND
ONE OF US HAD TO PULL OUT A WIN.
>> WE'RE ON THE BOTTOM, JEFF,
CIERA AND I.
IT'S TWO VERSUS THREE.
YOU DO FEEL THE PRESSURE.
SOMETIMES THINGS DON'T GO YOUR
WAY IN THE CHALLENGES BUT
THERE'S OTHER ASPECTS OF THE
GAME YOU CAN CONTROL.
>> Jeff: SO WHEN YOU GO BACK
TO CAMP, DO YOU SIT DOWN AND SAY
"ALL RIGHT, WHO DO WE THINK IS
THE ONE PERSON WE CAN GET TO
CRACK?"
>> NOT NECESSARILY CRACK BUT YOU
CAN FOCUS ON THE TRUTH AND
THERE'S ONE REASON WE'RE KEEPING
MONICA AROUND AND THAT'S BECAUSE
THEY THINK THEY CAN BEATER IN
THE END.
THEY DREW A ROCK BECAUSE TYSON
KNOWS IF MONICA ISN'T AROUND HE
CAN'T BEAT ANYBODY ELSE.
>> I DREW ROCKS BECAUSE I KNEW I
COULD TRUST MONICA TO THE END.
>> I'M SURE.
>> JEFF, ONE MAN'S PERCEPTION IS
ANOTHER MAN'S REALITY.
WHAT THEY PERCEIVE IS A REALITY
TO THEM BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT'S
REALLY GOING ON.
THAT IS WHAT PEOPLE DO ON THE
BOTTOM.
YOU START THROWING AS MUCH TRASH
AT THE WALL AND HOPE SOMETHING
STICKS.
>> Jeff: AND MONICA, LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL IS STUCK.
>> IT DID.
>> Jeff: DID THEY COME TO YOU,
MONICA?
>> YES, CIERA CAM AND FILLED ME
H SOME UNBECOMING TNGS
THAT HAD BEEN SAID BY GERVASE
AND TYSON.
>> Jeff: HOW DID THAT SIT WITH
YOU?
>> NOBODY LIKES TO HEAR NEGATIVE
THINGS ABOUT THEMSELVES.
>> DO YOU THINK THERE'S ANY
TRUTH WHAT SHE'S ALLEGING WAS
SAID ABOUT YOU?
>> PERHAPS.
AND THAT'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT THE ENTIRE WAY
HERE.
>> Jeff: TYSON, DOES IT
CONCERN YOU THAT CIERA MIGHT
HAVE BEEN SRING EITHER SECRETS
OR MAKING UP LIES?
>> IT DOES A BIT BUT CIERA AND I
TALKED AND I SAID "WHO DO YOU
WANT TO GO TO THE FINAL THREE
WITH?"
FIRST PERSON SHE SAID MONICA
BECAUSE SHE COULD BEAT HER.
I'M SURE SHE TOLD HER LIES.
BUT MONICA KNOWS WHAT KIND OF
CHARACTER I AM.
>> MONICA KNOWS WHAT KIND OF
CHARACTER YOU ARE TO HER FACE
NOT BEHIND YOUR BACK.
>> I TOLD MONICA WOMAN TO WOMAN
I WANT YOU TO KNOW WHO YOU'RE
PLAYING WITH AND WHEN YOU GET TO
THE FINAL THREE AND THEY BEAT
YOU SEE SITTING AT HOME
THE TRASH THEY'VE TALKED ABOUT
YOU TO GET YOU TO THAT POINT
YOU'RE GOING TO BE LIKE WHAT WAS
I DOING?
LIKE, THESE ARE VICIOUS, RUDE
THINGS AND IF IF YOU WANT TO GO
TO THE END WITH THAT I WOULD
STILL HAVE THE SAME RESPECT FOR
YOU BECAUSE YOU MADE IT TO THE
END BUT I FELT LIKE I WANTED YOU
TO KNOW.
>> IT'S FUNNY HOW THEY'RE
TELLING MONICA THIS STUFF NOW
WHEN THEY'RE DESPERATE TO STAY
IN THE GAME.
NOBODY SAID THIS STUFF TO MONICA
WHEN IT HAPPENED.
WHY NOT?
IF WE TALKED SO MUCH TRASH ABOUT
MONICA WHY WOULD YOU HOLD ON TO
THAT?
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE YOU'RE TRYING TO USE IT
TO YOUR ADVANTAGE.
>> JUST BECAUSE TYSON WAS IN
CONTROL OF THE GAME. CONTROLLING
MAJORITY OVER HERE.TROLLING THE
YOU'RESHED.
>> SO WHO'S CONTROLLING YOUR
ALLIANCE?
IS IT YOU?
>> YOU CAN TALK TO CIERA ABOUT
THIS?
>> YES OR NO?
IS IT YOU?
>> NO.
>> WHO IS IT THEN?
CIERA?
IT'S GOT TO BE ONE OF YOU GUYS.
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO BE I
OVER THERE BECAUSE IF NOT
THE PROBLEM AND THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE GOING HOME ONE BY ONE
>> OKAY, FIRST THIS.
GERVASE MAKING FUN OF MONA
BECAUSE I WAS THINKING NUMBER I
SAT HERE LASTTRIBAL COUNCIL
CONTROLLEDNT TO
STAND FOR IT AND I TO
KNOW HE HAS MADE FUN YOU, I
PROMISE YOU NOT JUST MADE FUN
EVIL RUDE THINGS HAVE BEEN SAID.
>> Jeff: HOW ARE YOU HANGI
IN THERE, MONICA?
IT'S THE PHRASE OF THE DAY.
"YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO D
DEEP."I'VE DONE.
I' YEARS OLD AND I'M FINDING
THAT SPACE DEEP DOWN D
DEEP AND I'M DOING IT AND
I DON'T KNOW WHAT MORE I
DO.CAN'T RESPECT THAT
I LIKE THESE PEOPLE AND THA
WHAT'S SO HARD AND SO
THAT CIERA TOLD ME TODAY?
HELL YES IT HURT ME.
AND A NEW SIDE OF ME HAS
OUT AND I JUST -- I'M RESILIENT
AND, YOU KNOW, MORALITY AND
ETHICAL ISSUES ARE GOING TO
>> Jeff: GERVASE, MONICA JUST
YOU'RE INGENUOUS
ETHICALLY THAT COULD BITEOU IN
THE ASS IN THE
NO MATTER HOW SURE YOU ARE
YOUR ALLIANCE, WHEN YOU HEAR
THINGS, YOUR MIND STARTS TO
THINK ABOUT IT.
WHAT CIERA WEEK, IT
PLAYS ON
HAPPEN THAT FAST.
>> Jeff: AND HAYDEN, THAT'S
WHAT YOU RELY ON.
GETTING INSIDE SOM
AND SHOWING THEM AETTER PATH
TO THE IN WHICH THEY CANN.
>> THAT'S THE TRUTH. TYSON HAVE
SUPERIOR GAME TO YOU.
>> I
>> AND THE PERCEPTION
HAVE, THE PERCEPTION THA
HAS IS THAT YOU'RE'S LAP
DOG AND THAT HE'S USING YOU ALL
END.
OPINION AND DO WE TALK THROUGH
IT?
>> MONICA, I LOVE YOU.
I HAVE RESPECT FOR YOU.
ALL I'M TELLING YOU IS
THEY'RE THAT MANIPULATIN
THEY TOLD ME MULTIPLE TIMES
"MONICA IS EASY, DO
WHATEVER I TELL HER TO DO."
THIS IS A MOMENT
"I MONICA CULPEPPER'S
GAME."
M.C.'S GAME RIGHT NOW
NOT ONLY THAT, A BIG MOVE YOU
YOUR FAMILY IS GOING TO BE
CHEERING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN WEIND
OURSELVES IN A VESTING
SITUATION.
IT IS VOTE.
HAYDEN, YOU'RE U
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, HAYDEN.
GERVASE.
HAYDEN.
THAT'S TWO VOTES HAYDEN.
GERVASE.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES HAYDEN; TWO VOTES
GERVASE.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. WATER"
HAYDEN.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GET THEM, GIRL.
>> GOOD GAME, FELLAS.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE, HAYDEN.
>> SEE Y'ALL LATER.
>> Jeff: WELL, AFTER TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL IT'S VERY CLEAR.
THERE'S A TIGHT ALLIANCE OF
THREE AND CIERA ON THE OUTSIDE.
THERE'S ONE WILD CARD:
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WHO'S COMING BACK AND HOW WILL
THEY CHANGE THE GAME?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON A
SPECIAL TWO HOUR SEASON FINALE.
>> DO OR DIE TODAY.
>> Jeff: ONE WILL RETURN FROM
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> I HAVE TO GET BACK IN THE
GAME.
>> Jeff: AND ONE WILL WIN THE
TITLE OF SOLE "SURVIVOR."
>> I WANT THE MILLION DOLLARS.
I WANT TO BE THE SOLE SURVIVOR.
I WANT THE TITLE.
>> Jeff: SUNDAY, DECEMBER 15.
>> HAYDEN!
HAY.
>> HELLO, HAY DIS.
>> OH!
>> I KNOW.
>> DANG IT!
>> TRIBAL TONIGHT WAS BRUTAL.
I FELT LIKE WE WERE CLOSE BUT
HERE I AM, MONICA DOING MONICA,
JUST LISTENING TO WHAT TYSON
SAYS.
MONICA IS A LAP DOG.
TYSON HAS HER ON A LEASH.