PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR:
THE RETURNING PLAYERS WERE IN
CONTROL OF THE GAME. THEY WERE
LED BY A MAJORITY ALLIANCE OF
FIVE.
THEIR ONLY WORRY WAS KNOWING
THAT THEIR LOVED ONES WERE BEING
VOTED OUT.
AND AT REDEMPTION ISLAND, BRAD
CULPEPPER WAS TAKING ALL THE
BLAME.
>> SHE'S SHUSHING THE WOMEN.
>> HAVE I SHUSHED A WOMAN.
>> ( BLEEP ) YOU, BRAD
CULPEPPER.
>> Jeff: FOR THE LOVED ONES,
THINGS WENT FROM BRAD BAD TO
WORSE.
WHEN THEY LOST THEIR FOURTH
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IN A ROW.
GALANG REMAINS UNDEFEATED.
>> I WANT MY DAUGHTER TO SUCCEED
YET I HAVE A TRIBE OF PEOPLE
COUNTING ON ME AS WELL.
>> Jeff: THE MEN PLANNED TO
TAKE OUT ONE OF THE GIRLS.
BUT CALEB CAUGHT WIND OF ANOTHER
PLAN.
>> CALEB.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, CALEB TOOK
THE GAME INTO HIS OWN HANDS.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO
HOME.
I'M GOING TO WRITE BRAD'S NAME
DOWN.
>> Jeff: WOW!
THAT IS THROWING IT OUT THERE.
QINGs TADHANA TO THROW OUT
THEIR LEADER, BRAD THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE BIGGEST
SHIFTS OF POWER THAT HAS EVER
HAPPENED AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
13 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
WOW, YOU GUYS.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BACK YOU ALL
INTO A CORNER THERE.
>> WOO.
>> I COULDN'T HELP.
>> WHAT THE HECK.
TRIBAL WAS UNREAL.
>> ARE YOU UPSET?
>> I LOVE SEAR ATOO.
IF THIS IS BRAD'S TIME IT'S
BREAD TIME.
>> NOW I SEE THAT THEY HAD NO
CLUE CALEB WAS GOING TO DO
THAT.
IF I CAN GET CALEB SWITCH OVER
TO ME AND KATIE, ME AND KATIE
HAVE THE NUMBERS.
EITHER WAY, I'M HAPPY TO BE HERE
ANOTHER DAY.
>> THAT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
>> TOUCHE.
GOOD STUFF.
>> DID YOU HAVE THAT PLANNED?
>> NO.
IT JUST FESTERED.
I THOUGHT IT HAD JUST FESTERED
UNTIL I JUST COULDN'T KEEP IT
DOWN.
YOU KNOW, GOING INTO TRIBAL, I
THOUGHT I DON'T REALLY FEEL GOOD
ABOUT BRAD ANY MORE.
I'M NEVER TRUST HIM AGAIN SO I
JUST BROUGHT IT OUT.
>> HUGE MOVE, BRO.
>> DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY, TO BE
HONEST.
I WAS BLOWN AWAY.
>> CALEB PULLED A FAST ONE, AND
DOING SO, KIND OF, LIKE, SCREWED
ME AND VYTAS.
>> CRAZY, CRAZY, CRAZY.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THAT MEANS
HE'S WITH THE GIRLS AND VYTAS
AND I ARE ON THE OUTS.
I HAVE NO CLUE WHERE I STAND
RIGHT NOW IN THE TRIBE.
>> WELL, CALEB MADE A GOOD
MOVE.
KUDOS TO HIM.
HE KNOWS THE GAME.
I GUESS HE LEARNED A LITTLE BIT
FROM COLTON.
I WAS A LITTLE NERVOUS BECAUSE I
KNEW JOHN AND CANDICE WERE
HERE.
I BLINDSIDE JOHN AND CANDICE HAD
CHOICE WORDS FOR ME THE LAST
TIME I SAW HER.
JOHN AND CANDICE.
BEFORE YOU GUYS HIT ME, I'M
WAVING THE WHITE FLAG.
SO YOU DON'T WAKE UP AND FREAK
OUT THAT I'M HERE.
CANDICE, I'M SORRY.
>> OKAY.
>> IT'S A GAME.
I DIDN'T WANT IT TO END UP THIS
WAY.
>> I WAS DEAD ASLEEP, AND I HEAR
THE SWEETEST VOICE THAT I
EVERMENTED TO HEAR ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND-- BRAD CULPEPPER.
>> I AM SHOCKED THAT YOU'RE HERE
HERE.
I EXPECTED TO SEE BRAD ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND AT SOME
POINT.
PEOPLE MAKE DECISIONS AND TRY TO
MAKE BOLD MOVES AND SOMETIMES IT
BITES THEM IN THE ASS.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT DID BITE BRAD
IN THE ASS.
A LITTLE VINDICATION THERE.
>> I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE ANGRY.
I APOLOGIZE FOR WHATEVER.
QUITE FRANKLY, I'M GLAD THAT I'M
NOT GOING TO GET ABUSED AND
IDEAL AT, AT REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> BRAD CAME IN TRYING TO SAY NO
HARD FEELINGS.
BUT HIS WIFE VOTE ME OUT ON DAY
ONE, AND HE VOTED JOHN WHEN JOHN
TRUST HIM.
I HAVE NO LOVE FOR HIM.
>> IT WAS ALL BUSINESS.
IT WASN'T PERSONAL AT ALL.
YOUR REAL ALLIANCE IS YOUR
SPOWRKS YOUR LOVED ONE.
>> BRAD CAN SAY ALL HE WANTS,
BUT IN THIS GAME, IT'S KILL OR
BE KILLED, AND HE'S ON OUR
ISLAND NOW, REDEMPTION PIEMED SO
I HAVE MY CHANCE TO PUT HIM OUT
OF THE GAME FOR GOOD.
>> WE CAN SEE!
( CHEERS )
>> OH, FEELS SO NICE.
>> YES, EVERYWHERE.
IN THIS GAME OF "SURVIVOR" YOU
NEED TOO GET A GROUP OF PEOPLE
THAT YOU TRUST AND YOU NEED TO
GET PEOPLE TO LIKE YOU.
AND THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO
IN THIS GAME.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, LAURA.
THIS IS SO NEEDED.
>> I LIKE ARAS.
AND WE LIKE BEING AROUND EACH
OTHER BECAUSE WE CAN JUST CALM
EACH OTHER.
I HOPE THAT ARAS HAS THE SAME
FEELING AND HAS THE SAME TRUST
IN ME THAT I HAVE IN HIM.
>> I LIKE NICE LATS, NICE
SHOULDERS.
>> I THINK LAURA M. SOMEHOW
THINKS SHE'S PLAYING ME BY
CUDDLING UP NEXT TO ME WHICH
COULDN'T BE FROM THE TRUTH.
I'M NOT THINKING THANKS FOR
FLIRTING WITH ME AND I'M GOING
TO GO AHEAD AND KEEP YOU IN MY
ALLIANCE.
>> OH, RIGHT THERE.
IT'S WHAT I NEEDED.
RIGHT NOW, ESSENTIALLY MY CORE
ALLIANCE IS ME, MONICA, TINA,
TYSON, GERVASE.
THAT'S THREE PEOPLE THAT AREN'T
IN, AND I THINK LAURA M., SHE'S
SMART, SHE'S PERCEPTIVE.
I THINK SHE KNOWS SHE'S ON THE
OUTS SO SHE'S DOING WHATEVER SHE
CAN TO GET HERSELF IN THE GOOD
GRACES OF THE PEOPLE SHE THINKS
WILL HELP HER GET FURTHER IN THE
GAME.
>> WHERE DID YOU LEARN TO DO
THIS, MAURA M.?
>> I'VE BEEN MARRIED 20 YEARS.
>> OH, NIGHT TIME AT CAMP.
ALL OF THE VETERANS ON THE TRIBE
HAVE THIS UNSPOKEN BOND.
THEY'VE ALL DONE "SURVIVOR"
BEFORE.
I HAVE NOT.
I'M STILL SLOWLY GETTING TO KNOW
EVERYONE.
GERVASE, I GOT BLANKY SPACE.
I GOT BLANKET SPACE.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> OKAY.
WELL, FOR FUTURE REFERENCE.
I DON'T HAVE THAT TOABLGTHS
EMOTIONAL CONNECTION THAT THEY
ALL HAVE, AND I STILL DO FEEL
LIKE THE OUTSIDER, THE NEW GIRL
IN TOWN.
IT MAKES THIS GAME VERY
DIFFICULT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GALANG, GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW TADHANA TRIBE.
BRAD VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
CANDICE, JOHN, AND BRAD.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> I CAN TAKE YOUR SPOT?
>> MONICA.
YOU'RE MY ROCK.
I ADORE YOU.
YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO TAKE MY
SPOT.
I'M GOING TO BATTLE.
I'LL GET BACK.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I'M SO INCREDIBLY SORRY.
>> HONEY, I ADORE YOU.
BUT I'M NOT HERE BECAUSE I'M A
JERK, AND I WANTED TO MAKE THAT
CLEAR TO EVERYBODY OVER THERE.
THESE GUYS ALREADY KNOW IT.
>> THIS TRIBE KNOWS IT, TOO.
>> Jeff: SO, BRAD, A LOT OF
THE NEGATIVE ENERGY THROWN YOUR
WAY CAME FROM CANDICE.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WHICH IS INTERESTING,
CANDICE, GIVEN THAT YOU'VE HAD
THE MOST TO SAY ABOUT CULPEPPER
AND A LOT OF THINGS GOING ON IN
BOTH TRIBES AND YET YOU HAVEN'T
SPENT A SINGLE SECOND AT EITHER
CAMP.
>> YEAH, I WAS JUST REPEATING
THINGS I HEARD FROM PEOPLE THAT
WERE VOTED OUT, AND THEY WERE
PRETTY ADAMANT ABOUT THE THINGS
THAT THEY SAID.
IT'S THEIR WORD AGAINST HIS.
>> AND HIS AND HIS AND HIS.
>> AND THEY'RE STILL IN THE
GAME.
>> AND HERS AND HERS AND HERS
AND HIS.
>> AND MAYBE THAT'S A REALLY
GOOD LESSON TO LEARN, CANDICE,
BECAUSE YOU REALLY HURT MY
FEELINGS, TOO, SCREAMING
OBSCENITIES--
>> MONICA, YOU HURT MY FEELINGS
WHERE YOU WROTE MY NAME DOWN.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET TO YOUR
DUEL.
MEERS HOW IT IS GOING TO WORK.
TAKE APART A CRATE AND USE THE
PLANKS TO BUILD A BRIDGE.
ONCE YOU COMPLETE THE BRIDGE,
YOU'LL TAKE APART THE BRIDGE AND
USE THE PLANKS TO SOFT PUZZLE.
FIRST TWO PEOPLE TO FINISH THEIR
PUD PUZZLE STAY ALIVE IN THIS
GAME, CONTINUE THEIR QUEST TO
GET BACK IN AND A SHOT AT THE
MILLION DOLLARS.
THE LAST PERSON TO FINISH IS OUT
FOR GOOD.
YOUR TIME IN THIS GAME IS OVER.
CANDICE, JOHN, BRAD.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
REGARDLESS, SOMEBODY IS ABOUT TO
LOSE A LOVED ONE.
MONICA IS GOING TO LOSE BRAD OR
JOHN AND CANDICE ARE GOING TO
USE OF LOSE ONE OR THE OTHER.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
THE FIRST STEP IS JUST TAKE THAT
CRATE APART.
BECAUSE THESE ARE THE PLANKS
YOU'RE GOING TO USE TO BUILD
YOUR BRIDGE.
CANDICE AND JOHN GOING TO START
WORK RIGHT AWAY.
BRAD GOING TO TAKE ALL HIS
PLANKS OUT AT ONCE.
>> BRAD, TAKE THEM FROM THE
BOTTOM UP.
>> Jeff: CANDICE OFF TO A
QUICK LEAD IN JUST ANOTHER
DUEL.
SHE HAS OWNED REDEMPTION ISLAND
ARENA.
NOBODY HAS BEAT CANDICE.
JOHN AND BRAD VYING FOR SECOND
RIGHT NOW, QUICKLY BEHIND.
>> LET'S GO, BRAD!
>> Jeff: CANDICE IS FLYING
THROUGH THIS.
JOHN IN SECOND, BRAD IN LAST
RIGHT NOW.
>> STAY CALM, BRAD.
>> Jeff: JOHN IS WRONG.
HE'S GOT TO HEAD BACK.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR FOR BRAD.
>> NICE WORK.
>> Jeff: BRAD NOW AHEAD OF
JOHN.
>> NICE, BABY, YOU'RE DOING
AWESOME.
>> Jeff: THIS IS VERY CLOSE.
NOBODY WANTS TO GO HAPPY.
TOO MUCH GAME LEFT TO PLAY.
WE'RE ONLY 11 DAYS IN.
CANDICE STARTED OUT WITH THE
LEAD EARLY.
NOW SHE'S SLOWING DOWN.
>> YOU'RE DOING AWESOME.
>> Jeff: WOW, WE ARE NECK AND
NECK.
LITERALLY, EVERYBODY PLACING
PIECES AT THE SAME TIME.
ONCE YOU FINISH YOUR BRIDGE,
THEN YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE IT
APART AND USE THESE PLANKS TO
SOLVE THE PUZZLE.
BRAD WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
JOHN WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
HE'S ONE AWAY.
CANDICE IS NOW IN THIRD JOHN
WILL BE THE FIRST TO FINISH HIS
BRIDGE.
YOU HAVE TO TOUCH HERE.
JOHN NOW GOING TO START TAKING
IT APART.
HE'S LOOKING FOR PLANKS THAT
HAVE PAINT ON THEM.
THEY'RE GOING TO HELP HIM SOLVE
THE PUZZLE.
>> GOOD JOB, BRAD!
GOOD JOB, BRAD!
>> Jeff: BRAD IS NOW DONE.
>> GOOD JOB, DARLING.
>> Jeff: BRAD IS NOW LOOK FOR
PUZZLE PIECES.
NOW CANDICE CAN TAKE HER BRIDGE
APART.
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR PIECES THAT
HAVE PAINT ON THE BOTTOM.
THOSE ARE THE ONES YOU NEED.
THE OTHERS YOU CAN DISCARD.
BRAD AND JOHN RIPPING THROUGH
THIS.
JOHN HAS ALL OF HIS PIECES.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU'RE DOING FANTASTIC.
>> Jeff: BRAD HAS ALL OF HIS
PIECES.
>> GO, CULPEPPER!
>> Jeff: MONICA GETTING A LOT
OF SUPPORT FOR HER HUSBAND.
WANDIS AND JOHN ONLY HAVE EACH
OTHER.
CANDICE HAS ALL OF HER PIECES.
YOU HAVE 12 HUSBANDLE PIECES.
YOU ONLY NEED EIGHT.
FOUR OF THEM DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
>> YING YANG IN THE MIDDLE.
>> Jeff: THIS IS IT.
TWO WILL STAY ALIVE.
ONE IS GOING HOME.
JOHN MAKING QUICK WORK ON HIS
PUZZLE.
JOHN HAS IT.
JOHN WINS A DUEL.
IT IS NOW CANDICE AND BRAD.
LOOKING FOR THE SECOND SPOT.
>> COME OBRAD!
>> THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT, EITHER.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER VERY
CLOSE.
>> GET THE YELLOW.
>> Jeff: CANDICE VERY CLOSE.
IT'S CANDICE AND BRAD RIGHT
NOW.
ONE WILL MOVE OONE WILL NOT.
>> COME OCULPEPPER!
>> PUT THE SIM BELL TOGETHER IN
THE MIDDLE.
>> GET THE SYMBOL TOGETHER, THE
YIN YANG.
REPLACE THE MIDDLE ONE YES, YES,
YES.
>> DONE, DONE, DONE!
>> Jeff: DOES BRAD HAVE IT?
BRADS THAT.
CULPEPPER STAYS ALIVE.
JOHN STAYS ALIVE.
CAND SISUTE CAND SIS OUT OF
THIS GAME.
JOHN CONGRATULATIONS, BRAD,
CONGRATULATIONS ON STAYING
ALIVE.
CANDICE, WHAT IS THE FEELING
NOW?
YOU'RE NOT ONLY LEAVING THE
GAME.
YOU'RE LEAVING YOUR HUSBAND OUT
HERE TO FIGHT FOR HIMSELF.
>> I THINK I'D HAVE TO SAY THIS
IS THE HARDEST.
YOU KNOW, I CAME OUT HERE WITH
MY LOVED ONE.
SO IT'S DIFFERENT THAN COME OUT
WITH 20 STRANGERS.
>> Jeff: JOHN, WHAT'S IT LIKE
FOR YOU, LESS THAN A FOOT
SEPARATES YOU FROM YOUR WIFE BUT
SHE'S ABOUT TO LEAVE AND YOU
WILL BE OUT HERE ALONE.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,UN HOW MUCH
SHE WANTS TO PLAY.
>> IT'S ABSOLUTELY MISERABLE.
I MEAN, THE HEARTBREAK IN SEEING
HER VOTED OUT FIRST BECAUSE I
KNEW HOW HARD THAT WAS FOR HER.
THEN NOT SWITCHING WITH HER, AND
NOW, LIKE, SENDING HER HOME,
IT'S JUST-- IT'S AWFUL.
>> Jeff: CANDICE, YOUR TIME IN
THIS GAME IS DONE.
YOU HAVE A GOOD-BYE WITH JOHN.
GO AHEAD AND HAVE IT.
>> WON'T OCCUR ABOUT ME.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW, YOU'RE
TOUGH.
GO HAVE SOME CHEESEBURGERS FOR
ME.
>> NO MORE TEARS, OKAY?
>> Jeff: REPORTER, CANDICE
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE URN ON
YOUR WAY OUT.
>> BYE, GUYS.
HAVE FUN.
BYE, JEFF.
( APPLAUSE )
LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JOHN,
BECAUSE YOU WON THE DUEL, YOU
GET TO DECIDE WHO GETS THE CLUE,
THE LOCATION OF AN IDOL.
I THINK I'LL GIVE IT TO MONICA
AGAIN.
>> Jeff: MONICA.
HERE'S YOUR CLUE.
NOW LAST TIME YOU THREW THIS
CLUE IN THE FIRE.
ARE YOU GOING TO KEEP THIS ONE?
OR ARE YOU GOING TO BURN IT
AGAIN?
>> THROW IT IN THE FIRE.
>> IT'S NO GOOD.
>> Jeff: JOHN, BRAD,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU STAY ALIVE.
YOU CONTINUE YOUR QUEST TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME AND ANOTHER
SHOT AT THE MILLION DOLLARS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AWAIT YOUR NEXT COMPETITOR AND
YOUR NEXT DUEL.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, HEAD ON BACK TO
CAMP.
>> THANKS FOR YOUR CHEERS AND
SUPPORT.
>> HE'S NOT OUT.
>> NO.
LISTEN, IT'S A GAME.
>> I WOULD BE VERY SURPRISED IF
HE DIDN'T COME BACK IN THE
GAME.
>> WELL, THANK YOU FOR YOUR
WORDS OF ENCOURAGEMENT.
TODAY WAS PROBABLY THE MOST
DEMORALIZED I HAVE BEEN OUT
HERE.
I DIDN'T THINK BRAD WAS GOING TO
BE THERE.
BUT HE'LL BE FINE.
HE'LL PULL HIMSELF UP BY HIS
BOOT STRAPS AND HE'LL COME OFF
THAT REDEMPTION ISLAND AND WE
CAN MEET UP AND SCRAMBLE OUR WAY
TO THE END.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S "SURVIVOR."
WE'RE THE SAME PERSON.
IF ONE OF US IS HERE, WE'RE BOTH
HERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> HOWEVER IT TURNS OUT.
>> BRAD AND MONICA ARE A VERY
TIGHT COUPLE.
AND THAT'S VERY THREATENING.
>> I FEEL GOOD.
I FEEL FINE.
BRAD'S THERE.
IF HE CAN JUST HANG ON A LITTLE
BIT MORE, AND COME BACK, FROM
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> YUP.
>> AND WE SEE HOW IT ALL GOES.
BUT, PLEASE, KNOW, THAT DOESN'T
AFFECT MY SITUATION WITH YOU AND
I HOPE THAT DOESN'T AFFECT YOUR
SITUATION.
>> I THINK MONICA REALIZES SHE
DOESN'T HAVE HER GUY OUT HERE AS
A BACKUP ANYMORE.
SO I THINK SHE'S GOING TO STEP
UP HIR GAME PLAY A LITTLE BIT.
>> I THINK THAT OUR GROUP WILL
STAY ALIVE, AND THEN AFTER THE
MERGE, ZEAL TO SEE WHO HAS GOT
LOVED ONES AND DO THEY COME IN?
DO THEY GO OUT?
WHERE DO THEY STAND?
>> I CAN'T SAY 100% TRUST
MONICA.
SHE'S EITHER GOING TO BE A BIG
THREAT OR SHE'S GOING TO BE A
GREAT ASSET.
I JUST HAVEN'T DETERMINED WHICH
ONE OF THESE SHE IS YET.
>> SO WE'RE GOOD.
>> HE'S NOT A DUMB JOCK.
HE'S A LAWYER, TOO.
>> YUP.
>> IF NOBODY ELSE DOES, I'LL
HAVE IT.
>> IT'S ALL YOU.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR," THERE
ARE SO MANY LAYERS TO IT.
THERE'S THE BASIC LAYER OF STROG
SURVIVE, HAVING TO FIND FOOD,
HAVING TO FIND SHELTER, DEALING
WITH THE HEAT.
>> THIS SAND IS HOT.
>> I HAVEN'T, YOU KNOW, BRUSHED
MY TEETH.
AND THEN TO HAVE ON TOP OF THAT
INJURIES, WHETHER IT BE SCRAPES
ON OUR LEGS.
I'M COVERED IN BUG BITES.
I'VE NEVER HAD SO MANY ON MY
FACE OMY NECK, ON MY BACK.
WE'RE BEAT UP.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT COULD GET ANY
WORSE.
AT THIS POINT WE'RE LOSING.
WE'RE, YOU KNOW, SLOWLY OUR
BODIES ARE DISINTEGRATING.
WE'VE HAD IT ROUGH.
>> THIS IS-- ALONG HERE IS
IRRITATED.
FROM WEARING WET SHOES ALL THE
TIME I GOT 10IA, IT'S LIKE
ATHLETE'S FOOT.
IT BURNS.
YOU GET LITTLE SORES AND THEY
CAN VERY PAINFUL WHEN YOU WALK,
AND IT'S UNDER YOUR TO NAILS.
I LOST A TOW NAIL.
>> YOU LOST A TOENAIL?
>> OH, MAN.
THAT'S GONNA FALL OFF.
>> YEAH, IT'S, LIKE, COMING
OFF.
DISGUSTING.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU COULD BREAK
HER TOES OFF.
THAT'S WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE.
THEY'RE RED.
THEY'RE CRUSTING.
HER TOENAILS ARE FALLING OFF.
>> THIS TOENAIL FELL OFF TOO.
>> IT'S NOT SOMETHING I CHOOSE
TO LOOK AT BECAUSE IT SINGS ME A
LITTLE BIT BUT I FEEL BAD FOR
THE GIRL.
>> THEY DEFINITELY LOOK
IRRITATED.
>> WE'RE ALL LICKING OUR
WOUNDS.
OUR EGOS ARE STILL A LITTLE
BRUISED BY ALL THE LOSING.
IF WE KEEP LOSING, HOW DO I
ALIGN MYSELF AT THIS POINT?
HOW IS THIS GOING TO SHAKE OUT,
AND HOW DO I MAKE SURE TO COME
OUT ON THE OTHER SIDE AS
UNSCATHED AS POSSIBLE?
I LOVE CIERA, SHE'S SUCH A
SPUNKY LITTLE GIRL, MAN. MAN.
>> THERE'S NO POINT IN THIS GAME
WHERE ANYBODY WILL BE 100% WITH
CALEB AFTER WHAT HE DID.
SOMEBODY WHO CAN TURN ON A DIME
LIKE THAT.
AS CALEB DID IN TRIBAL COUNCIL
VOTING OUT BRAD IS SOMEBODY YOU
HAVE TO REALLY FINESSE AND MAKE
SURE THEY FEEL OKAY
EMOTIONALLY.
IT'S SO COOL OUT HERE.
LIKE, THOSE TWO GIRLS IN REAL
LIFE WOULD NEVER EVEN MEET LET
ALONE GET ALONG WITH EACH OTHER,
YOU KNOW.
OUT HERE, THEY'RE THICK AS
THIEVES, THOSE TWO, BEST
FRIENDS.
BUT SAME THING ME AND YOU, MAN.
LIKE, WHEN WOULD WE EVER
CONNECT?
>> I CAN READ PEOPLE PRETTY WELL
BUT I CAN'T QUITE GET A READ ON
CALEB.
YOU KNOW, A QUIET WOODSMAN FROM
ALABAMA.
IT'S IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW THEY
ENSURE CALEB IS STILL WITH ME.
SO, YOU KNOW, OF COURSE I'M
TRYING TO BE NICE TO CALEB.
( LAUGHS ).
>> AFTER BLINDSIDING BRAD, I'M
IN A POSITION TO WHERE I COULD
SWING WITH THE GIRLS OR I COULD
SWING WITH THE GUYS.
DO I FEEL POWERFUL NOW?
I THINK THE WORD IS I'VE
OCCURRED IS BIG KAHONAS.
I THINK I HOLD A LOT OF POWER
WITH MY VOTE.
IT'S GOOD TO BE THE SWING VOTE.
BEEN SO PEACEFUL.
THERE'S JUST A DIFFERENT ENERGY
AROUND CAMP.
I LIKE HEARING THE NATURE.
I LIKE ENJOYING THIS LAGOON.
AND BRAD, A LOT OF THE NOISE HE
CAME WITH KIND OF POLLUTED IT.
JUST ENJOYING THIS PEACE AND
QUIET IS GREAT, MAN.
I'VE NEVER BEEN ANYWHERE MORE
BEAUTIFUL.
>> YEAH.
LOSING STREAK HAS GOT TO END
SOMETIME.
>> YEAH.
>> WHATEVER HAPPENS TODAY, YOU
GUYS, WE'VE JUST GOT TO TRY AS
HARD AS WE CAN.
WE HAVE TO WANT IT MORE THAN
THEY WANT IT.
SO JUST TRY OUR BEST AND NO
MATTER WHAT KIND OF CHALLENGE IT
IS, I THINK WE CAN WIN.
>> I'M SO NERVOUS GOING INTO
THIS CHALLENGE.
IF WE LOSE THE CHALLENGE TODAY
AND WE HAVE TO COME BACK HERE
IT'S SCRAMBLE TIME AGAIN BECAUSE
EVERY SINGLE WEEK I HAVEN'T
STEPPED UP AND THIS IS MY LAST
SHOT.
TO WIN THIS NEXT CHALLENGE WOULD
BE SWEET AND PERFECT TIMING FOR
US-- PERFECT TIMING.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR THE FOURTH
STRAIGHT TIME, I WILL TAKE BACK
THE IDOL FROM GALANG.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ONE
MEMBER OF EACH TRIBE WILL RACE
DOWN A GIANT "SURVIVOR" SLIDE,
GRABBING A RING ALONG THE WAY.
YOU WILL THEN TOSS THE RING,
ATTEMPTING TO THRAND ON A POST.
FIRST PERSON TO LAND THEIR RING
SCORES A POINT FOR THEIR TRIBE.
FIRST TRIBE TO FIVE WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTE OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION, ARE YOU PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: JUICY STEAK.
( CHEERS )
VEGETABLES.
SPICES.
AND A WOK TO COOK IT ALL UP IN.
>> A WOK!
>> Jeff: OR IF YOU WANT YOU
CAN TRADE IT FOR FISHING GEAR.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: TADHANA HAS YET TO
WIN A CHALLENGE.
THIS WOULD BE A TOUGH DECISION.
GALANG, YOU HAVE THREE EXTRA
MEMBERS.
SITTING THREE PEOPLE OUT.
YOU CAN SIT OUT ANYBODY YOU
WANT.
>> I'M NOT SITTING OUT.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER WHO'S GOING
TO SIT OUT?
MONICA, LAURA, LAURA.
ATTACK A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> I HATE SITTING OUT.
>> ME, TOO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO.
FIRST ROUND, IT IS GERVASE FOR
GALANG TAKING ON CALEB FOR
TADHANA.
TADHANA HAS YET TO WIN A
CHALLENGE IN THIS GAME.
COULD THIS BE THE ONE?
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GO, CALEB!
GERVASE HAS HIS RING.
CALEB MISSES HIS.
GOT TO LAND IT ON ONE OF THE
FIVE POSTS.
GERVASE JUST MISSES.
CALEB DOES IT WITH HIS FIRST
TOSS.
TADHANA OFF TO AN EARLY LEAD.
1-ZIP.
NEXT TWO, WE HAVE TYSON FOR
GALANG TAKE ON HAYDEN FOR
TADHANA.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BOTH GUYS FLYING DOWN.
BOTH GUYS COME UP WITH THEIR
RINGS.
HAYDEN TOSSES AND MISSES.
TYSON JUST MISSES.
JUST MISSES FOR HAYDEN.
TYSON SCORES FOR GALANG.
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
KAT FOR GALANG.
TAKING ON KATIE FOR TADHANA.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BOTH CHEM FLYING DOWN THE
SLIDE.
KAT COMES UP WITH HER RING,
KATIE MISSES HERS.
BIG ADVANTAGE FOR KAT RIGHT OUT
OF THE GATE.
CAN SHE TAKE ADVANTAGE?
JUST MISSES.
>> KAT JUST MISSES.
>> KATIE SCORES FOR TADHANA.
TADHANA LEADS 2-1.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: WE HAVE A REMASM,
BROTHER AGAINST BROTHER.
LAST TIME ARAS WON IN A VERY
PHYSICAL SHOWDOWN.
>> IT WAS AWESOME.
>> Jeff: IT IS ARAS VERSUS
VYTAS.
TADHANA LEADS 2-1.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: BOTH GUYS COME UP
WITH THEIR RINGS DEAD EVEN.
AND JUST LIKE THAT WITH ONE
TOSS, VYTAS SCORES FOR TADHANA.
TADHANA LEADSES 3-1.
>> DAMN IT!
>> Jeff: NEXT ROUND, TINA FOR
GALANG.
CIERA FOR TADHANA.
TADHANA LEADSES 3-1, PLAYING TO
5.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
CIERA COMES UP WITH HER RING.
TINA HAS HERS.
CIERA TOSSES JUST MISSES.
CIERA COULD PUT TADHANA AHEAD
4-1.
NO.
ALL AROUND IT?
>> Jeff: TINA SCORES FOR
GALANG!
CLOSES THE GAP.
>> GOOD JOB, TINA.
>> Jeff: TADHANA LEADS 3-2.
EVERYBODY'S GONE ONCE.
NOW EVERYBODY STARTS AGAIN.
NEW MATCH-UP.
THIS TIME IT IS CALEB TAKING ON
TYSON.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
TYSON COULD TIE IT UP RIGHT
HERE.
CALEB COULD PUT THEM AHEAD.
CALEB STRUGGLE FOR HIS RING.
TYSON HAS HIS.
JUST MISSES.
>> CALEB JUST MISSES.
>> Jeff: TYSON WITH A NICE
LITTLE LAUNCH BUT SHORT.
CALEB SCORES FOR TADHANA.
TADHANA LEADS 4-2.
>> CALEB, YOU'RE THE BEST.
>> Jeff: NEXT ROUND, HAYDEN
GOING UP FOR TADHANA.
GOING TO TAKE ON GERVASE FOR
GALANG.
>> COME ON, GERVASE!
>> Jeff: THIS COULD BE FOR
TADHANA.
>> PLEASE!
>> Jeff: THIS IS AS CLOSE AS
THEY HAVE EVER BEEN TO WINNING A
CHALLENGE IN THIS GAME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: THEY'RE ONE POINT
AWAY.
HAYDEN CAN WIN IT FOR HIS
TRIBE.
>> CROSS EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> COME ON, HAYDEN!
>> Jeff: HAYDEN NOT MESSING
AROUND.
HE IS UP QUICKLY.
GERVASE MISSES HIS.
HAYDEN JUST MISSES.
GERVASE TOSSES AND MISSES.
HADEEP TOSSES AGAIN.
NO!
GERVASE HAS GOT TO SCORE FOR
GALANG.
HAYDEN SCORES!
TADHANA WINS THEIR FIRST
CHALLENGE OF THIS SEASON!
IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
>> FINALLY!
>> WE FINALLY WON!
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
GOOD EFFORT.
>> THANK YOU, JESUS.
>> Jeff: TADHANA, FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN THIS GAME,
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
( APPLAUSE )
AND FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THIS
GAME, YOU WILL NOT GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU HAVE TWO CHOICES ON REWARD.
WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> STEAK.
>> Jeff: TAKING THE STEAKS.
COME GET YOUR REWARD.
ENJOY IT.
GIVING UP THE CHANCE TO FEED
THEMSELVES FOR THE REST OF THE
GAME IN ORDER TO FEED THEMSELVES
RIGHT NOW.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
ENJOY YOUR REWARD.
CONGRATS, TADHANA.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: GALANG, FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN THIS GAME, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTE OUT OF THIS TRIBE.
THEY WILL BE SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND WHERE THEY WILL HAVE TO
COMPETE IN DUELS FOR A SHOT TO
GET BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SIGH TONIGHT IN TRIBAL.
STEAK.
>> WE DIDN'T REALLY STAND A
CHANCE IN THAT ONE.
>> IT IS MY FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THESE GUYS HAVE EXPERIENCED IT,
SO THERE'S THE NERVES, FIRST OF
ALL, OF GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND THEN THE NERVES OF OH, MY
GOD, IT COULD BE ME.
THE FIRST TRIBE OUSTED ME RIGHT
AWAY.
AND WHO'S TO SAY THIS TRIBE
WON'T, TOO.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD.
I'M TRYING TO RELAX.
HOPEFULLY IT WILL ALL WORK OUT
OKAY.
I'LL STILL BE HERE.
I'M STILL PACKING.
JUST TO BE SURE.
SO TODAY, MY STRATEGY IS JUST
BEING VERY AWARE, KEEPING MY
EYES OPEN ALL THE TIME ON WHOSS
WITH WHO, WHAT'S GOING ON, YOU
KNOW, AND JUST TRY TO MIX IT UP.
>> OH!
>> LET US PRAISEGOD FOR THE
DELICIOUS FRUIT HE PUTS ON THIS
PLANET FOR US TO SAVOR.
ABOUT ME?
WHO?
>> GIRLS, YOU KNOW, GIRLS HAVE
RIVALRIES.
I FELT IT THE WHOLE TIME.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> WAIT, WHAT?
>> THE GIRLS WANTED TO DO THE
CHALLENGE.
>> NOBODY LIKES SITTING OUT.
THAT'S HOW IT GOES.
>> WELL, THAT SUCKS.
>> LAURA, I'M LIKE WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I LOOK TO MY LEFT, I LOOK AT
TYSON.
HE'S BAFFLED.
WHEN YOU KNOW SOMEONE'S AT THE
BOTTOM, ALL YOU CAN DO IS
ACCOMMODATE THEIR CONVERSATION,
MAKE THEM FEEL BETTER.
NO WORRIES.
SHE'S AT THE BOTTOM SO SHE'S
GOING TO SAY WHATEVER SHE WANTS
TO SAY.
>> I JUST THOUGHT I'D THROW THAT
OUT THERE.
OH, WOMEN.
>> WE HAVE THE CORE ALLIANCE OF
ME, ARAS, GERVASE, TINA, AND
MONICA.
WE'RE A SOLID FIVE.
KAT ALSO FEELS LIKE SHE'S IN
THAT ALLIANCE OF FIVE.
>> ALL RIGHT, HOLD THAT UP AND
I'LL POUR.
AND LAURA MAURA HAS NO CLUE WHAT
ALLIANCE IS GOING ON.
BUT RIGHT NOW, THE PLAN IS TO
VOTE OUT SOMEONE THAT EVERYBODY
IS SUPER ANNOYED WITH.
AND THAT'S LAURA B.
>> THIS GAME IS FUN.
I DIDN'T KNOW I'D HAVE THIS MUCH
FUN.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT DO YOU
THINK WE SHOULD DO?
WHAT'S THE CONSENSUS?
>> I THINK LAURA B IS THE
OBVIOUS ONCE.
>> NOBODY HAS TO BE WORRIED OR
PANIC.
>> LOCK IT DOWN.
>> ARAS IS THE ONE I COMPLETELY
EXPLICITLY TRUST IN THIS GAME.
WE DON'T TALK A LOT OF STRATEGY,
WE DON'T NEED TO.
DROP A NAME, TELL ME WHO IT IS
AND LET'S DO THIS.
>> LAURA B TONIGHT.
IT SHOULD BE 7 VOTES TO 1,
DONE.
LAURA B IS A VERY EASY VOTE
OUT.
EVERYONE FEELS UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH HER, BUT RIGHT NOW, EASY
VOTES ARE OFTEN THE DUMBEST VOTE
IN THIS GAME.
JUST BECAUSE IT'S EASY DOESN'T
MEAN YOU SHOULD DO IT.
>> LAURA B.
>> RIGHT NOW, MONICA'S GOT HER
HUSBAND ON REDEMPTION ARENA, AND
IF BRAD SHOULD LOSE AT
REDEMPTION ARENA AND NOT COME
BACK IN THIS GAME SHE'S A
WONDERFUL ASSET TO HAVE.
LAURAM GREAT IN CHALLENGES,
GREAT AT PUZZLES.
IF SHE'S SHOOE GOES TO
REDEMPTION ARENA AND KNOCKS OUT
BRAD, MONICA IS OURS.
LAURA M. SEES THE BEST CHOICE
RIGHT NOW.
>> THINK ABOUT IT.
AND THEN GET BACK TO US.
>> OKAY, I'M GOING TO THINK
ABOUT IT.
THERE ARE LOTS OF DIFFERENT
THINGS TO THINK ABOUT.
>> LAURA M.'S NAME IS BEING
THROWN AROUND.
COULD SHE BEAT BRAD AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND?
THAT'S MY WORRY.
>> ARE YOU OKAY WITH THAT?
>> @AN ODD POSITION I'M IN.
LAURA B WOULD BE AN EASY WIN AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND FOR BRAD.
LAURA M.?
SHE'S GOING TO BE A CHALLENGE.
YOU KNOW, WHAT ABOUT LAURA B.
>> MAYBE THE EASY VOTE.
>> IT'S AN EASY VOTE, AND YOU
DON'T STIR UP CONTROVERSY.
>> TONIGHT, I WANT LAURA M. TO
GO HOME, BUT IT'S NOT ONLY MY
DECISION.
IT'S THE TRIBE'S DECISION.
AND PEOPLE ON MY TRIBE KNOW THAT
I'M PLAYING THE GAME.
AND THE MORE THAT I TRY TO
MANIPULATE A VOTE, THE MORE
DANGER I PUT MYSELF IN.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH YOU IS A
TORCH.
GRAB THE TORCH, APPROACH THE
FLAME, DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST TIME.
GERVASE, IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE YOU PLAYED THIS GAME.
IT HAS CHANGED A LOT.
>> I MEAN, THIS IS CRAZY THAT
I'M HERE AGAIN IN FRONT OF THIS
FIRE, IN FRONT OF YOU.
IT'S VERY SURREAL TO ME.
I CAME INTO THIS GAME THINKING I
COULD PLAY IT A CERTAIN WAY, BUT
THAT IS DEAD AND GONE.
THAT'S 13 YEARS AGO.
THAT'S NOT NOW.
THESE PEOPLE MAKE MOVES.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE WHEELING AND
DEALING FROM DAY ONE, LIKE,
EITHER I NEED TO GET ON BOARD,
OR I NEED TO GO HOME.
>> Jeff: TINA, YOU GO BACK ALL
THE WAY TO THE SECOND SEASON.
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE FROM YOUR
VANTAGE POINT AS ONE OF THE
ORIGINATORS OF THIS GAME?
>> YOU KNOW, JEFF, I REMEMBER
THINKING ON DAY 5 I HAD PLAYED
MORE IN FIVE DAYS THAN I PLAYED
MY ENTIRE SEASON IN AUSTRALIA.
IT'S GOING THAT QUICKLY.
AND THE "BLOOD VERSUS WATER"
THING, I MEAN, IF YOU'RE PLAYING
THIS GAME JUST YOU, YOU CAN PLAY
BALLS TO THE WALL.
BUT IT'S NOT JUST YOU.
>> Jeff: SO, MONICA, HOW DOES
IN "BLOOD VERSUS WATER" TWIST
CHANGE THE GAME?
>> THE STAKES ARE HIGHER.
EVERY TIME GUTO A DUEL NOW FOR
ME, I'M LOOKING OUT THERE FOR MY
LOVED ONE.
AND THEN PEOPLE START THINKING,
WELL, WHO HAS MORE POWER WHEN
THEY GET TO THE MERGE AND
THEY'RE PERHAPS PLAYING WITH A
LOVED ONE?
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN THEY BECOME
A TEAM OF TWO.
SO IT MAKES THE STRESS IN THE
GAME TWOISES -- MUCH.
>> Jeff: OARAS, THAT LOYALTY
OF WHETHER A LOVED ONE WILL VOTE
THEIR LOVED ONE OUT OR NOT IS
ONE OF THE BIG FACTORS.
>> IT'S A BIG FACTOR.
YOU MAKE AN ALLIANCE, AND THEN
YOU WONDER IN WHOIN MY ALLIANCE
MIGHT GO WITH THEIR LOVED ONE.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE ALL THAT INTO
CONSIDERATION.
BUT RIGHT NOW, LET VYTAS DO WHAT
VYTAS DOES AND MAYBE THERE'S
SPACE FOR HIM OR MAYBE THERE'S
NOT.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE I SHORE UP
ALL OF THESE RELATIONSHIP.
>> Jeff: ARAS SAYS MY LOVED
ONE IS ON HIS OWN.
IT'S THE ONLY THING YOU CAN
SAY.
>> IT'S THE TRUTH.
THERE'S A TIME WHEN YOU HAVE TO
CUT THE APRON STRINGS AND SAY,
SEAR AYOU HAVE TO FLY ON YOUR
OWN.
YOU CAN'T LIVE UNDER MY WING
ANYMORE.
IT SOUNDS REALLY COLD AND HARD
BUT RIGHT NOW THIS IS OUR
BLOOD.
>> Jeff: AND, GERVASE, LAURA
M. COULD MAKE A GOOD ARGUMENT
SHE'S PROVEN SHE WILL SQUASH HER
DAUGHTER AS SHE HAS REPEATEDLY
IN CHALLENGES.
DOES THAT GIVE YOU A SENSE OF
HER LOYALTY TO THIS TRIBE?
>> HONESTLY, SPENDING TIME WITH
LAURA M., AND HEARING HER TALK
ABOUT CIERA, THEY'RE CLOSE.
AND THAT'S GREAT TO HEAR, BUT
IT'S ALSO THREATENING.
UN, IT'S FOR EVERYBODY HERE--
MOTHER-DAUGHTER, BROTHERS,
BOYFRIEND-GIRLFRIEND, OR HUSBAND
AND WIVES.
IT DOESN'T GET TIGHTER THAN
THAT.
>> Jeff: LAURA B., YOU WERE
VOTED OUT SECONDS INTO THE
GAME.
YOU'RE NOW ON A TRIBE OF PEOPLE
WHO PLAYED BEFORE.
YOU HAVE NEVER PLAYED.
DO YOU BELONG OUT HERE?
>> WELL, JEFF, I FEEL VERY MUCH
A PART OF THIS TRIBE.
AND A PART OF THE DECISION
MAKING AND A PART OF THE PLAY.
I WORK HARD.
I AM A BIG PART OF THIS TRIBE,
AND I THINK I'VE SHOWN THAT.
SO I DO BELONG HERE.
OF COURSE, I BELONG HERE.
>> Jeff: MONICA WOULD YOU
AGREE WITH THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SHE WAS WITH US DAY ONE.
SHE IS A PART OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING.
SHE FISHES.
SHE DOES FIRE.
SHE DEFINITELY HAS A PLACE IN
THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: AND LAURA B., THAT'S
WHAT THEY ALWAYS SAY TO SOMEBODY
BEFORE THEY VOTE THEM OUT--
GREATEST TRIBE MEMBER EVER.
>> THERE IS ALWAYS THE BACKSIDE
I COULD BE AN EASY VOTE.
I WAS WELCOMED WITH OPEN ARMS
BUT I DID SEE THE DISAPPOINTMENT
IN MY TRIBE'S EYES.
>> Jeff: DO YOU GET THAT,
LAURA B., EVEN THOUGH YOU WANT
TO PLAY, YOU'RE NOT RUPERT.
RUPERT IS TIE DYE, MAN IN THE
WOODS.
>> BUT THE CONFIDENCE IN ME
THINKS I'M SUCH A HUGE PART OF
THIS TRIBE, AND I'VE BONDED WITH
THESE PEOPLE I FEEL LIKE.
THAT'S ALL I CAN SAY.
>> JEFF, HERE'S THE OTHER
THING.
SHE HASN'T BEEN TO THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL BEFORE SO SHE HASN'T
FELT THE STING OF YOU PUTTING
THE TORCH OUT AND SAYING THE
GAME IS OVER.
THAT'S STILL STINGING IN EVERY
SINGLE ONE OF US.
SHE HASN'T HAD THAT.
>> Jeff: I CAN'T THINK OF A
BETTER LEAD-IN.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
LAURA M., YOU'RE UP.
>> IT'S BEEN REALLY GREAT
PLAYING WITH YOU, BUT THERE'S
ONLY ROOM FOR ONE LAURA ON THIS
ISLAND.
>> I'M SO SORRY THAT SOMEBODY
HAS TO GO HOME.
BUT I'M REAL HAPPY TO HAVE ONLY
ONE LAURA ON THE TRIBE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY TNOW WOULD BE THE TIME SOOD
SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LAURA B.
LAURA M..
THAT'S TWO VOTES LAURA M., ONE
VOTE LAURA B.LAURA M.THAT'S
THAT'S THREE VOTES LAURA M.
>> LAURA M..
THAT'S FOUR VOTES LAURA M., ONE
VOTE LAURA B.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. WATER,"
LAURA M.PERFORM THAT'S FIVE,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
I WOULD EXPECT NOTHING LESS FROM
A GROUP OF RETURNING PLAYERS
THAN A BLINDSIDE STRAIGHT OUT OF
THE GATE AND IT ILLUSTRATES YOU
CAN NEVER PREDICT WHAT IS GOING
TO HAPPEN NEXT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME
ON "SURVIVOR":
>> Jeff: GERVASE AND TYSON ARE
READY TO MAKE A MOVE.
>> THAT'S THE TRICKY PART, WHEN
TO DETHRONE KING ARAS.
>> Jeff: BUT NOT EVERYTHING
GOES AS PLANNED.
AFTER 14 DAYS WE'RE GOING TO
SWITCH THINGS UP.
>> I WAS ABSOLUTELY SHOCKED,
BLINDSIDED.
HELLO?
>> HELLO.
>> IT'S LAURA.
>> HOW THE HELL DID YOU GUYS
LOSE?
>> I TRUSTED SOME PEOPLE IN THE
GAME THAT I SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
TRUSTING.
BUT I'M STILL IN THE GAME.
THE GAME IS NOT OVER.
I GOTTA KEEP MY WITS ABOUT ME.
I HAVE TO WIN THE DUEL.