>> Jeff: FROM DAY ONE, THE
RETURNING PLAYERS DOMINATED
THEIR LOVED ONES.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT COULD GET
ANY WORSE.
>> Jeff: SENDING THEM TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, WEEK AFTER WEEK.
JOHN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
HE HAS THE RING AND HE'S UP WITH
IT.
BUT AFTER 13 DAYS, THE LOVED
ONES FINALLY WON A CHALLENGE.
HAYDEN SCORES.
TADHANA WINS THEIR FIRST
CHALLENGE OF THIS SEASON.
BACK AT CAMP, LAURA B WAS THE
EASY TARGET.
>> WHO DO YOU WANT YOU WOULD
WANT TO SEND HOME FIRST?
>> LAURA B.
>> Jeff: BUT ARAS HAD BIGGER
PLANS.
>> Jeff: THE TRIBAL COUNCIL,
GALANG WENT WITH ARAS AND TOOK
OUT ONE OF THEIR STRONGEST
COMPETITORS.
LAURAM.
HOPING LAURAM CAN BEAT BRAD AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND'S NEXT DUEL.
LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
WILL GALANG GET BACK TO WINNING
OR WILL VOTING OUT LAURAM
BACKFIRE?
12 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> THAT WAS BRUTAL.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK ABOUT YOUR
FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL, LAURA?
>> IT WAS SAD TO SEE SOMEBODY
VOTED OUT FIRST.
>> I'M GLAD IT WASN'T ME.
WE JUST GOT BACK FROM MY FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND I'M BACK.
I'M BACK HOME.
IT WASN'T ME.
MY NAME WAS WRITTEN DOWN, BUT WE
ALL HAD A UNANIMOUS VOTE TO VOTE
OUT LAURAM TONIGHT.
>> I FEEL LIKE AN OCTOPUS.
WE WERE EIGHT LEGS STRONG AND
NOW WE'RE DOWN A LEG.
>> RUPERT GAVE UP HIS GAME TO
LET ME PLAY.
I THINK HE'S GOING TO BE SO
PROUD OF ME.
>> SHE LOOK AT ANYBODY?
>> I DIDN'T LOOK AT HER.
>> SHE LOOKED ME DEAD IN THE EYE
LIKE, "YOU'RE A JERK.
OF.
>> WHY DID YOU LOOK AT HER?
>> WHY DID I LOOK AT HEAR?
I KIND OF WANTED TO SEE HER
EXPRESSION.
I WAS CURIOUS.
LAURAM LOOKED ME DEAD IN THE
EYE, AS SHE REALIZED IT WAS HER,
AND SHE WAS VERY ANGRY, AND I
GOT MY FINGERS CROSSED THAT
SHE'S GOING TO TAKE THE NOBLE
APPROACH TO REDEMPTION ARENA,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, REDEMPTION
ARENA HAS BECOME A PLACE TO
DESMIMP PEOPLE'S CHARACTER.
>> DO YOU THINK WE'RE GOING TO
GET THE RAMIFICATIONS OF ALL
THIS TOMORROW?
>> WHAT IS SHE GOING TO SAY?
SHE HADERATE WAYS OF THE WAY
THAT VOTE WAS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT.
SHE KIND OF DID HERSELF IN.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT LOOKS LIKE I'M
THE RING LEADER.
THAT'S NEVER A GOOD THING.
YOU NEVER WANT TO BE AT THE TOP.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO GET OUT OF
THAT POSITION.
PUT ONE FOOT IN FRONT OF THE
OTHER, TREAD CAREFULLY, I
SUPPOSE.
WE HAVEN'T REALLY HAD A CHANCE
TO TALK ONE ON ONE ABOUT ARAS.
I FEEL OKAY WITH HIM RIGHT NOW.
>> UH-HUH.
>> BUT IF WE LOSE, THERE'S A
GOOD CHANCE THAT'S THE LAST TIME
BEFORE THE MERGE.
>> YEAH.
>> THE SECOND HE GOES WITH
VYTAS, I'M THINKING HE THINKS
I'M A THREAT.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHICH IS DANGEROUS.
THAT MEANS WHEN HE GET TO VYTAS,
HE'LL BE LIKE, "TYSON IS
TROUBLE."
>> YOU FIGURE ARAS CAN MAKE A
MOVE.
>> AND DOES THAT SCARE JEW OF
COURSE.
>> SO WE'RE BOTH KIND OF ON THE
SAME PAGE WITH HIM?
>> RIGHT.
>> I DO LIKE ARAS.
HE'S A GREAT GUY.
HE'S FUNNY.
HE'S A LITTLE OUT THERE ON HIS
ZEN-TYPE BELIEFS BECAUSE I HAVE
ZERO BELIEFS-- EXCEPT FOR MAGIC.
I BELIEVE IN MAGIC.
IT'S AWESOME.
BUT PEOPLE LIKE ARAS, THEY DO.
THAT'S THE TRICKY PART, WHEN TO
DETHRONE KING ARAS.
IF WE LOSE THE CHALLENGE WOULD
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM WRITING HIS
NAME DOWN?
>> LESS AS IT GOES ON.
ARAS IS A LEADER RUNNING THE
SHOW, AND TYSON BROUGHT UP GOOD
POINTS THAT WE MAY ONLY HAVE ONE
MORE CHALLENGE LEFT BEFORE THE
MERGER, AND THAT MAY BE OUR LAST
CHANCE TO GET RID OF ARAS.
>> IT'S SOMETHING TO THINK
ABOUT.
IF YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH
HIM, I'M GOING TO FEEL GREAT
WITH HIM, TOO, OR I'M GOING TO
TRY TO FEEL GREAT WITH HIM.
I WANT TO DO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
BECAUSE I'M IN WITH THIS YOU.
>> I ABSOLUTELY SCREWED UP IN MY
FIRST SEASON BEING A CHESS PIECE
AND THAT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
JUST TO BE LOOKED AT AS A PLAYER
WHO PLAYED IT TWICE AND DIDN'T
PLAY.
I DON'T WANT THAT.
I THINK THE NEW POWER COUPLE OUT
HERE IS ME AND TYSON.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
TADHANA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW GALANG TRIBE.
LAURA M. VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE'RE NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL.
JOHN, BRAD, AND LAURAM.
SO CIERA, EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE THE
ROOKIE, YOU SURVIVED FOUR TRIBAL
COUNCILS.
YOUR MOM, THE VETERAN, DIDN'T
SURVIVE ONE.
>> IT'S WEIRD BECAUSE ALL DAY
I'VE HAD A REALLY WEIRD FEELING.
I JUST-- I JUST KIND OF KNEW.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
>> Jeff: DOES THAT SURPRISE
YOU, LAURA, THAT SHE MIGHT
ACTUALLY HAVE FELT SOMETHING,
SOME ENERGY?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
THAT'S MY BABY.
SHE CAME FROM ME.
SHE'S PART OF ME.
WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE STILL IN THIS.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE TWISTS
THIS SEASON IS THAT IF YOU HAVE
A LOVED ONE THAT IS ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND, YOU CAN SWAP
SPOTS--
>> THERE'S NO WAY SHE'S SWAPPING
WITH ME.
NO WAY IN HELL.
>> Jeff: YOU WOULDN'T EVEN
HEAR OF IT.
>> NOT EVEN HEAR OF IT.
I GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE CONFIDENT
YOU'RE GOING TO GET BACK IN?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO TODAY'S DUEL.
FOR TODAY'S DUEL, YOU'RE GOING
TO RACE ACROSS THE BALANCE BEAM,
COLLECTING BAGS OF NUMBERED
TILES, YOU MUST THEN PLACE THE
TILES IN ORDER, 1-100.
THE FIRST TWO TO FINISH LIVE TO
SEE ANOTHER DAY.
ONE STEP CLOSER TO GETTING BACK
IN THIS GAME, AND A SHOT AT THE
MONEY.
LAST PERSON TO FINISH IS OUT FOR
GOOD.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNER OF THE
DUEL WILL DECIDE WHO GET THE
CLUE TO THE LOCATION OF THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST TWO TO FINISH STAY ALIVE,
LOSER IT OUT.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU GOTTA STAY ON THE BEAM.
YOU CAN ONLY UNDO ONE BAG AT A
TIME.
LAURA OFF TO A FAST START.
WHIPPING THROUGH THOSE KNOTS.
JUST HAS TO GET ACROSS THE BEAM,
AND SHE DOES.
JOHN HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
BRAD HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
THE FIRST BAG CONTAINS 10 NUMBER
TILES.
YOU HAVE TO PUT THEM IN ORDER.
LAURA HAS HER FIRST 10.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
JOHN MAKING QUICK WORK ON HIS
PUZZLE.
JOHN HAS HIS FIRST 10.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
BRAD TAKE A LITTLE MORE TIME.
LAUREN AND JOHN BOTH WORKING ON
THEIR SECOND BAGS.
JOHN ALMOST FALLS OFF.
LAURA HAS THE SECOND BAG.
JOHN FELL OFF.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
THAT OPENS THE DOORT FOR BRAD.
IT'S NOW JOHN AND BRAD NEX OF
NECK AND NECK FOR SECOND PLACE.
LAURA WITH A LEAD NOW.
JOHN DROPS HIS SECOND BAG.
BRAD NOW AHEAD OF JOHN.
>> PERFECT.
>> Jeff: OH!
JOHN FALLS OFF.
HAS TO GO BACK.
THAT'S GOING TO HURT AND LEAVE A
MARK.
YOU HAVE 20 NUMBER PIECES IN
THIS BAG.
YOU'RE DOING 11-30.
JOHN IS ACROSS NOW WITH HIS
SECOND BAG.
LAURA HAS HER SECOND SET
COMPLETED.
>> GOOD JORK MOM.
>> Jeff: BRAD AND JOHN SIDE BY
SIDE, NECK AND SCHNECK, WORKING
ON THEIR SECOND BAG.
LAURA WITH HER THIRD BAG,
EXTENDING THE LEAD.
THERE ARE 30 PIECES IN THIS BAG.
JOHN'S FINISHED HIS SECOND BAG.
JOHN IN SECOND.
BRAD IN LAST RIGHT NOW.
IT IS LAURA IN THE LEAD, BRAD
AND JOHN BATTLING IT OUT FOR
THAT SECOND SPOT TO STAY ALIVE
OUT HERE.
JOHN MAKES QUICK WORK OF HIS
THIRD BAG.
BRAD HAS IT.
HE'S WORKING ON HIS THIRD BAG.
LAURA FINISHES HER THIRD BAG.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: LAURA PREDICTED, "I
GOT THIS.
OF VERY CLOSE TO THIS PREDICTION
COMING TRUE.
JOHN FINISH HIS THIRD, NOW
HEADING FOR HIS FOURTH AND FINAL
BAG.
BRAD FINISH HIS THIRD.
HE'S GOT TO PICK IT UP.
LAURA ON HER FOURTH AND FINAL
BAG.
JOHN HAS HIS FOURTH BAG.
BRAD HAS HIS FOURTH AND FINAL
BAG.
>> GOT IT, BABY.
>> Jeff: LAURA WITH A BIG
LEAD.
THIS IS ALL SHE HAS LEFT, THE
80s, AND 90'S.
JOHN IS AT 75.
BRAD IS AT 68.
YOU ARE VERY CLOSE.
>> DONE.
>> Jeff: LAURA HAS IT!
LAURA WINS THIS DUEL AND WILL
STAY ALIVE ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IT IS NOW DOWN TO BRAD AND JOHN.
ONE SPOT LEFT.
JOHN NOW AT 90.
BUT BRAD IS QUICKLY CATCHING UP.
>> HUGE COMEBACK, BRAD.
>> Jeff: IT IS BRAD AND JOHN
NECK AND NECK.
IT'S GOING TO COME DOWN TO THE
LAST FEW NUMBERS.
JOHN WILL STAY ALIVE, GINE
LAURA, IN THEIR QUEST TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
BRAD CULL PERRER IS OUT AFTER 14
DAYS.
( APPLAUSE )
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> Jeff: LAURA M.,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU CALLED IT FROM THE
BEGINNING.
ABSOLUTELY CONFIDENCE.
JOHN, YOU STAY ALIVE.
BRAD, YOU'VE PLAYED IN ARGUABLY
THE BIGGEST AREININ SPORT,
PROFESSIONAL FOOTBALL.
HOW DOES THE COMPETITION OF
"SURVIVOR" COMPARE TO THAT?
>> WELL, I'D LIKE TO THINK I HAD
MORE OF AN ADVANTAGE IN
FOOTBALL.
MONICA, I CAME ON HERE AS A
SHIELD.
THROUGH MY FAULT OR NO FAULT OF
MY OWN, I PROBABLY BECAME AN
ANCHOR.
YOU'RE FREE.
THE WIND'S BLOWING.
SAIL.
SAIL HARD.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BRAD.
YOUR TIME IN THIS GAME IS OVER.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF, AND
TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE URN ON
YOUR WAY OUT.
>> I LOVE YOU, SWEETIE.
I AM GOING TO HAVE TO DO THIS
ALL BY MYSELF.
NOW THEY DON'T HAVE BRAD ANYMORE
TO SOFTEN WHATEVER BLOWS OR TO
HELP ME OUT OR HAVE MY BACK, I
HAVE TO THINK ABOUT ME.
THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAURA M.,
BECAUSE YOU WON THE DUEL, YOU
NOW ARE IN CHARGE OF WHO GET THE
CLUE TO THE LOCATION OF A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
I'LL GIVE IT TO VYTAS.
>> Jeff: WHY NOT YOUR
DAUGHTER?
>> WE ALL KNOW IT'S A TARGET ON
YOUR BACK.
>> Jeff: CLUE TO THE LOCATION
OF AN IDOL.
AND YOU'RE FOLLOWING ME RIGHT
DOWN TO THE FIRE.
NOBODY WANTS THE IDOL.
DIDN'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
>> NOBODY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, AFTER 14
DAYS, YOU WILL LIVE TO SEE DAY
15.
LURA M., JOHN, GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
AWAIT YOUR NEXT COMPETITOR AND
NEXT DUEL.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> GREAT JOB, JOHN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TBA AND
TADHANA, BEFORE I SEND YOU BACK
TO YOUR CAMP, ONE MORE PIECE OF
BUSINESS.
AFTER 14 DAYS, OF PLAYING
AGAINST YOUR LOVED ONES, WE'RE
GOING TO SWITCH THINGS UP.
>> OH!
PLAYING AGAINST YOUR LOVED ONES,
WE ARE GOING TO SWITCH THINGS
UP.
YOU CAN DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE GOING TO DRAW FOR NEW
TRIBES.
>> GEEZ!
>> Jeff: TAKE THEM OFF AND SET
THEM DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, I HAVE NEW BUFFS IN
HERE.
THEY'RE ALL COVERED.
DON'T OPEN THEM UNTIL I TELL YOU
TO.
>> I CAN TAKE MINE LAST, JEFF.
I'LL LET FATE DECIDE WHERE I'M
AT.
>> Jeff: SURE, TYSON.
TYSON WANTS TO GO LAST.
TYSON WILL LET FATE DECIDE.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY, LET'S
REVEAL.
ARAS GOING TO SWITCH TRIBES.
A LOT OF GALANG STAYING
TOGETHER.
GERVASE IS GOING TO SWITCH
TRIBES.
TYSON IS GOING TO SWITCH TRIBES.
VYTAS AND KATIE WILL MOVE OVER
TO GALANG.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR TWO NEW
TRIBES.
ON GALANG, IT IS MONICA, TINA,
KATIE, LAURA B, KAT, AND ONE
GUY, VYTAS.
FOR TADHANA, IT IS THE OPPOSITE.
WE HAVE GERVASE, CALEB, ARAS,
TYSON, HAYDEN, AND ONE WOMAN,
CIERA.
CIERA, YOU WERE ONE OF ONLY TWO
WOMEN.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU NOW THE ONLY
WOMAN.
>> IT CAN EITHER BE A REALLY
GREAT THING OR A REALLY BAD
THING.
WE'LL FIND OUT.
>> Jeff: KATIE, YOU'RE PLAYING
WITH YOUR MOM.
>>IN, I'M REALLY EXCITED AND I
HAVE ANOTHER TRIBE MEMBER HERE,
TOO.
AND I'M EXCITED TO GET TO KNOW
THESE PEOPLE.
WE'LL SEE HOW IT ALL PANS OUT.
>> Jeff: VYTAS ON THE OTHER
SIDE, YOU'RE THE ONLY MAN.
>> I FANCY MYSELF A LADIES' MAN,
JEFF, SO THIS IS THE PERFECT
PLACE FOR ME.
>> Jeff: WE HAVE OUR TWO NEW
TRIBES.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD ON OUT.
THE GAME HAS CHANGED AGAIN.
>> I HAVE WORKED REALLY HARD THE
FIRST 14 DAYS OF THIS GAME, AND
THE TRIBE SWITCH PUT ALL THAT IN
JEOPARDY.
I HOPE I HAVE ENOUGH PEOPLE ON
MY SIDE WITH THE SWITCH THAT I'M
NOT ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> WELCOME TO TADHANA, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> THIS AIN'T BAD.
>> THIS IS PRETTY DARN GOOD.
>> LOOKS REAL GOOD.
>> THIS BEACH, I THINK, IS WAY
COOLER THAN OURS.
>> COMING BACK FROM REDEMPTION
ISLAND WITH THREE NEW
TRIBEMATES, IT'S A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
YOU DON'T KNOW REALLY WHAT TO
EXPECT.
NOW IT'S 3-3.
IT EVENS THE PLAYING FIELD OVER
HERE.
IF WE WERE TO LOSE A CHALLENGE
AND GO TO TRIBE, ARE WE THREE
GOING TO STICK TOGETHER?
ARE THEY THREE GOG STICK
TOGETHER?
WHAT INFORMATION ARE THEY GOING
TO GIVE BUWHAT WENT ON OVER
THERE?
AND HOW MUCH INFORMATION ARE YOU
GOING TO SHARE ABOUT WHAT WENT
ON OVER HERE?
>> WHAT HAPPENED ON THIS SIDE?
HOW DID THE VOTES GO DOWN?
>> WE BLINDDECIDED JOHN.
HE WENT OUT.
>> DID YOU PLAY AN IDOL OR SWAP?
>> NO, IT WAS SO INTENSE.
>> AS SOON AS WE GOT HERE, WE
TRIED TO DO A LITTLE FISHING TO
FIND OUT WHAT WAS REALLY GOING
ON IN THEIR TRIBE.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF TADHANA
REALLY REALIZED THAT'S WHAT WE
WERE DOING, BUT THEY STARTED
GIVING UP THE GOODS.
>> JOHN HAD THE CLUES, AND HE
WOULD STAY GONE FOR THREE, FOUR
HOURS.
>> DID HE FIND IT, DO YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> HE KIND OF TOLD BRAD, AND
THEN WE KIND OF GOT PIECES OF
THE CLUE.
>> WHAT WERE THE CLUES LIKE IN.
>> "ON THE WAY TO FRESH WATER."
>> THE ROOTS OF A SERPENT-LIKE
TREE.
>> HAYDEN AND CALEB GAVE THE
CLUE OF THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
TO ME.
IS IT JUST BECAUSE THEY'RE NEW
GUYS HERE AND HAVEN'T PLAYED THE
GAME BEFORE?
I DON'T KNOW.
STUPID WILL BE STUPID.
>> YOU GUYS SHOULD SEE ALL THE
VEGGIES WE HAVE LEFT.
>> SHOULD WE EAT THEM?
>> I THINK WE'RE GOING TO DO A
RICE VEGGIE.
>> WITH THOSE SPICES, THE RICE
IS GOING TO BE WAY GOOD, I BET.
>> THREE BIG GOODZ START GOING
THROUGH THE CUPBOARD, TAKING OUR
SEASONING, EATING OUR FOOD.
AND IN THE BACK OF MY MIND I'M
THINKING, "THAT'S MY STUFF,
DUDE!"
>> GRAB A FEW FOR ME, AS WELL.
>> I'M GOING TO GRAB A WHOLE
BALL.
>> AWESOME.
I WANT TO SMACK YOUR HAND AND
SAY MIND FIND YOUR OWN FOOD.
BUT YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
>> THERE ARE SOCIAL FAUX PAS TO
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR," AND ONE
IS EATING MORE FOOD THAN
EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> TYSON, YOU CAN DO US A FAVOR
AND OPEN UP A COCONUT WE COULD
ENJOY IN THE WATER?
>> YEAH, I WILL DO THAT.
BUT IF YOU COME IN AND THINK
EVERYBODY CRACKS OPEN A COCONUT
WHENEVER THEY WANT.
EVERYBODY CAN EAT A BANANA
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE FAIR.
WANT TO SEE HOW FAST I CAN DRINK
THIS?
IT'S DEFINITELY A GOAL TO EAT
AND STEAL AS MUCH FOOD AS I CAN
FROM THIS TRIBE, AND I'M GOING
TO KEEP EATING THAT FOOD TILL
IT'S GONE.
OH, IT'S TOO MUCH.
YOU DO HAVE TO DO A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF WORK OR APPEAR TO BE
WORKING SO THAT PEOPLE DON'T
JUST HATE YOU AS THE LAZY GUY.
>> YEAH!
ALL RIGHT!
THANK YOU.
>> I DON'T THINK I'M PAINTED AS
THE LADY GUY YET.
BECAUSE AFTER I CRACK A COCONUT
AND DRINK HALF OF IT, I PASS THE
REST AROUND TO THE OTHER FIVE
PEOPLE TO SHARE SO THAT'S KIND
OF GENEROUS FOR ME TO DO.
I'M GOING TO HIT ALL THAT FOOT
FOODLIKE A ONE-MAN WRECKING
BALL.
( LAUGHTER )
>> WELCOME TO OUR HOME.
THIS IS OUR HOUSE.
>> THIS IS KATIE.
VYTAS.
>> HI.
>> THIS IS MONICA.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
IT'S SO WONDERFUL TO HAVE KATIE.
THIS IS A CREAM COME TRUE.
THAT FIRST NIGHT I THOUGHT THIS
MIGHT BE THE ONLY NIGHT SHE AND
I SPEND TOGETHER.
AND HERE WE ARE TOGETHER AGAIN.
AND TO BE ABLE TO PLAY THIS GAME
WITH HER AND PLAY AS A TEAM IS
JUST WONDERFUL.
BECAUSE NOW, YOU SWITCH.
I'VE BEEN PLAYING WATER, AND NOW
I CAN PLAY BLOOD.
>>.
>> I WAS REALLY DISAPPOINTED
WITH WHAT HAPPENED.
I MEAN, I CAME FROM A PLACE
WHERE I WAS PRETTY MUCH IN
CONTROL OF MY DESTINY TO A PLACE
WHERE I HAVE ZERO CONTROL.
I MEAN, YOU COULD SAY, YEAH, TWO
OF US CAME OVER TO A GROUP OF
FOUR.
BUT IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE BECAUSE
ONE OF US THAT CAME OVER IS THE
DAUGHTER OF ONE OF THE FOUR.
SO YOU TAKE KATIE WITH TINA,
THERE'S ME AND THERE'S FIVE
GIRLS.
YOU KNOW, I'M THE ODD MAN OUT.
>> I THINK WE STICK TOGETHER IN
OUR TRIBE OF FOUR, THE ORIGINAL
GALANG.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I MEAN, YEAH, IT SOUND GOOD.
>> I MADE AN ALLIANCE WITH TINA,
MONICA, LAURA B, AND KATIE, BUT
MONICA WILL NOT STOP
STRATEGIZING.
SHE'S DRIVING ME CRAZY.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
I HAVEN'T EYE HAVEN'T MADE
THOSE--
>> IF WE WERE TO LOSE, IT WOULD
BE MAYBE VYTAS?
>> WHEN YOU HAVE AN ALLIANCE,
DON'T OVER-STRATEGIZE.
ALL THAT DOES IS PUT HE'S HEATON
YOUR BACK.
YOU WANT TO LEARN HOW TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR?"
SHUT IT.
>> LOOK AT ALL THE CENTIPEDES
COMING OUT OF THAT THING.
ALL THE DANGEROUS ANIMALES WERE
IN THAT LOG.
>> THIS THAT LOG.
WE KILLED ALL OF THEM.
>> ARE YOU GUYS HUNGRY?
SHOULD WE DO SOME RICE.
>> YES.
>> WE'RE ALWAYS HUNGRY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TELL YOU HOW
TO RUN YOUR HOUSEHOLD, GUYS.
>> BUT YOU FEED YOUR GUESTS
IMMEDIATELY.
YOU'RE BEING RUDE.
>>
>> BEFORE THE TRIBE SWAP,
GERVASE AND I HAD DECIDED THAT
GETTING RID OF ARAS MIGHT BE A
WISE MOVE.
SO NOW I JUST MAKE IT LOOK LIKE
HE'S BOSSING EVERYBODY AROUND,
TAKING CHARGE AND DOING WHATEVER
HE WANTS.
>> YOU KNOW, I'LL APOLOGIZE FOR
HIM CONSTANTLY.
I'M LIKE, "SORRY ABOUT ARAS.
HE KIND OF DOESN'T KNOW.
HE'S SOCIALLY UNAWARE, AN" AND E
SURE PEOPLE KNOW BETWEEN HE AND
I, HE'S THE ONE IN CHARGE.
>> YOU NEED MORE SUNSHINE.
>> THOUGHT ABOUT THAT.
BUT I WAS LIKE I ALREADY CUT
HALF OF IT.
>> I'M OUT HERE TO PLAY AND I
HAVE TO USE MY BRAIN.
SO HOPEFULLY IT WILL BE A LITTLE
SMALLER ON ME AND LARGE OR ARAS.
EVERYTHING YOU'VE GIVEN US AND
PLEASE BLESS THOSE WHO ARE NOT
AS FORTUNATE AS WE ARE.
AS OF RIGHT NOW, WE ARE A SOLID
TRIBE AND WE'RE GOING TO DO VERY
WELL TOGETHER AND PLEASE LOOK
AFTER OUR LOVED ONES WHO ARE ON
THE OTHER SIDE IN YOUR NAME,
AMEN.
>> IT IS ME AND FIVE WOMEN ON
THE NEW GALANG TRIBE, AND
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF PLAY FOR ME
COMING IN HERE.
BASICALLY, THESE WOMEN HAVE
BONDED SO I'M AT THE MERCY OF
THEM.
>> I WAS TRYING TO SAY
MISUNFORTUNATE-- BUT--
>> LESS FORTUNATE.
YOU KNEW WHAT I MEANT.
>> PINT OF LANGUAGE IS TO GET
THE IDEA ACROSS.
I GOT THE IDEA.
I DON'T KNOW THAT MUCH ABOUT
WOMEN.
BUT I DO KNOW THAT WHEN I'M A
LITTLE BIT VULNERABLE WITH
WOMEN, IT GOES A LONG WAY.
ME OPENING UP AND LETTING THEM
KNOW A LITTLE BIT ABOUT MY PAST
COULD KEEP ME AROUND.
>> HOW LONG WERE YOU IN JAIL?
>> I DID EIGHT MONTHS MY YEAR.
>> HOW SCARED WERE YOU?
>> SO SCARED.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M THIS LITTLE 19-YEAR-OLD KID
ON THE WEST SIDE.
EAST L.A., I KILLED THREE
PEOPLE.
I ROBBED FOUR BAEKS.
AND I'M LIKE I TRIED TO GET
MONEY FROM A LAELD FOR DRUGS.
>> HEARING VYTAS ADMIT HE HAD A
REALLY HARD TIME WITH A HEROINE
ADDICTION IS REALLY POWERFUL.
THAT'S A NEAT PART OF A MAN THAT
CAN SHARE HIS EMOTIONS AND
FEELINGS.
IT REMINDS ME OF RUPERT.
>> ARAS HAD SO MUCH RESENTMENT.
I ABANDON HIMAISE TEENAGER.
I WASN'T THERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> FOR THE LAST 13 YEARS NOW
IT'S BEEN US TRYING TO GET OUR
RELATIONSHIP BACK BECAUSE I LOVE
HIM.
MORE THAN ANYTHING, THAT'S WHO I
WANT TO HAVE A RELATIONSHIP
WITH.
ARAS IS SMATTER THAN ME.
ARAS IS MORE PHYSICALLY GIFTED
THAN ME.
ARAS IS AMAZING.
>> DON'T SELL YOURSELF SHORT.
>> I'M NOT SELLING MYSELF SHORT.
>> I AM SO ENJOYING GETTING TO
KNOW YOU.
DON'T SELL YOURSELF SHORT.
>> I LOVE VYTAS.
I FEEL CONNECTED ALREADY.
I HAVE TO KEEP MY HEART OUT OF
IT.
I LIKE HIM A LOT, BUT VYTAS AND
ARAS COULD TAKE THIS WHOLE GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
AS NEW TRIBES?
>> YES.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAKE BACK THE IMMUNITY EYEOL.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ONE PAIR
FROM EACH TRIBE WILL RACE OUT TO
A CAGE AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
OCEAN.
YOU'LL DIVE DOWN, RELEASE A
GATE, RETRIEVE A FISH TRAP, SWIM
IT BACK TO SHORE, THEN THE NEXT
PAIR GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL THREE
FISH TRAPS, YOU'LL USE THE
PIECES INSIDE TO SOLVE A
VERTICAL PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
YOU WANT TON WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>>
>> YES!
>> Jeff: IT'S PICNIC DAY ON
SURVIVOR.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: TURKEY, ROAST BEEF,
HAM.
YOU'VE GOT CHEESE, BREAD, ALL
THE TOPPINGS, BROWNIES.
SHOULD MAKE FOR A VERY NICE
AFTERNOON, ESPECIALLY KNOWING
YOU WON'T HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS GERVASE AND ARAS FIRST FOR
TADHANA.
LAURA B, AND TINA FOR GALANG.
YOU'VE GOT TO SWIM OUT TO YOUR
CAGE, RELEASE THE GATE, AND
RETRIEVE THE FISH TRAP.
GERVASE WITH A GREAT EFFORT.
HIS SWIMMING HAS IMPROVED QUITE
A BIT FROM DAY ONE.
GERVASE UP WITH THE GATE!
ARAS HAS THE TRAP.
SWIMMING IT BACK WITH GERVASE.
GALANG IS UP WITH THEIR FIRST
GATE.
LADIES!
TINA AND LAURA B SWIMMING BACK
WITHOUT THEIR FISH TRAP.
THAT'S GOING TO BE A PAINFUL
REALIZATION.
>> THEY FORGOT IT.
>> Jeff: WHEN THEY REALIZE
THEY FORGOT THE MOST IMPORTANT
PART OF THIS CHALLENGE.
>> YOU FORGOT THE TRAP!
>> Jeff: TINA AND LAURA STILL
HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THEIR TRIBE IS
TALKING ABOUT.
JARVIS AND ARAS ARE BACK WITH
THEIR FIRST FISH TRAP.
>> YOU FORGOT THE TRAP.
>> Jeff: SOMEBODY HAS TO GET
THE FIRST TRAP.
A HUGE CATASTROPHE FOR THE NEW
GALANG.
TYSON AND CALEB IN THE WATER
NOW, AND A HUGE LEAD FOR
TADHANA.
>> Jeff: LAURA B AND TINA
FINALLY MAKING THEIR WAY BACK.
A GIGANTIC LEAD FOR TYSON AND
CALEB.
LAURA B AND TINA NOW BACK WITH
THEIR FIRST FISH TRAP.
CALEB AND TYSON RACING BACK WITH
THEIR SECOND FISH TRAP.
IT'S MONICA AND VYTAS NOW IN THE
WATER FOR GALANG.
>> GO, GO, GO.
VYTAS UNDERWATER QUICKLY UNTYING
KNOTS.
HE KNOWS HE HAS A LOT OF TIME TO
MAKE UP.
>> COME OHAYDEN!
>> Jeff: GALANG HAS RELEASED
THEIR SECOND GATE.
MONICA AND VYTAS NOW SWIMMING
THAT TRAP BACK.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> HAYDEN AND CIERA HEADING BACK
WITH THEIR THIRD AND FINAL FISH
TRAP.
GALANG HEADING BACK WITH THEIR
SECOND, VYTAS AND MONICA, TRYING
TO MAKE UP SOME TIME.
>> WAY TO GO, GUYS, WAY TO GO.
NOW KAT AND KATIE IN THE WATER
FOR GALANG.
CIERA COMPLETELY SPENT.
... HER TRIBE CAN'T START
UNTYING UNTIL SHE IS BACK.
ALL RIGHT, PUZZLE MAKERS, START
UNTYING!
IT IS ARAS AND TYSON WORKING ON
THE PUZZLE FOR TADHANA.
>> THEY'RE NOT EVEN OUT TO THE
TRAP YET TADHANA WITH A HUGE
TIME ADVANTAGE.
ALREADY UNTYING ALL OF THEIR
PUZZLE PIECES.
LADIES NEED TO KEEP MOVING!
THEY'RE TRYING TO CLOSE THAT
GAP.
KAT AND KATIE HAVE THE THIRD
FISH TRAP.
THEY HAVE TO SWIM IT BACK NOW.
BUT THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
REALLY JAM TO CATCH UP TO
TADHANA.
>> GOOD JOB, GIRLS!
>> KAT AND KATIE BACK WITH THAT
THIRD FISH TRAP.
START UNTYING.
IT IS TINA AND MONICA WORKING
FOR GALANG.
ARAS AND TYSON WITH A HUGE TIME
ADVANTAGE, WORKING FOR TADHANA.
TINA WOULD LOVE TO BE ABLE TO
MAKE UP FOR THE COSTLY MISTAKE
SHE MADE AT THE BEGINNING.
>> THAT'S TMONICA.
>> Jeff: BY BRINGING HER TRIBE
BACK DURING THE PUZZLE
CHALLENGE.
>> SHOULD I MOVE IT OVER.
>> Jeff: SUDDENLY, TYSON AND
ARsAS ARE HAVING TROUBLES.
TINA AND MONICA NOW GAINING.
IT WOULD BE ONE OF THE BIGGEST
COMEBACKS IN THIS GAME.
WHICH IS WHY YOU NEVER GIVE UP.
>> RIGHT THERE, RIGHT THERE!
>> STEP BACK AND LOOK AT IT.
THE TAIL IS WRONG.
TADHANA HAD A HUGE LEAD AND THEY
HAVE TBLOAN IT.
WE ARE NOW NECK AND NECK.
YOU NEVER 99 "SURVIVOR."
MONICA AND TINA STILL WORKING.
IT WOULD BE A GIGANTIC COMEBACK
IF THEY COULD WIN THIS CHALLENGE
AFTER THE WAY IT STARTED.
GALANG THINKS THEY HAVE IT.
>> WE GOT IF!
>> Jeff: THEY DO NOT HAVE IT.
SOMETHING'S JUST NOT QUITE
RIGHT.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR FOR ARAS AND
TYSON.
ONE OF THE MOST BACK.
AND-FORTH CHALLENGE.
IT IS ANYBODY'S CHALLENGE TO WIN
RIGHT NOW.
MONICA AND TINA REARRANGING
AGAIN.
DO THEY HAVE IT NOW.
THEY DO NOT.
GALANG IT IS NOT RIGHT.
BACK TO WORK.
TYSON AND ARAS THINK THEY HAVE
IT.
AND THEY DO!
WINNING IMMUNITY, AND REWARD!
>> WOW!
>> GOOD EFFORT.
>> Jeff: TADHANA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
NOTRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
IN ADDITION, NICE PICNIC
AFTERNOON.
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO HAVE A
GREAT DAY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: GALANG, GOING TO BE
AN INTERESTING AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL TONIGHT
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS TRIBE AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> ON THE INSIDE, I'M SO
FRUSTRATED WITH TINA AND LAURA
B.
I WOULD HAVE NEVER MADE A
MISTAKE LIKE THAT.
I SHOULD HAVE GONE FIRST.
SOMETHING SHOULD HAVE HAPPENED
DIFFERENT, BUT I CAN'T ACT OUT
ON THAT.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY I'M SO
SORRY.
IF IT'S ME TONIGHT, I DON'T
BLAME YOU.
IF IT'S SOMEBODY ELSE, I FEEL
HORRIBLE GUILT.
BECAUSE I FEEL PARTLY
RESPONSIBLE FOR WHOEVER IS GOING
HOME.
AND I'M SORRY.
THAT'S ALL I KNOW TO SAY.
>> YOU WERE SO CLOSE.
>> YOU NEVER GAVE UP.
>> IT TOOK EVERYTHING IN ME TO
NOT LET THEM KNOW HOW I ACTUALLY
FELT ABOUT THE MISTAKE THEY
MADE.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR MERCY.
FOR YOUR MERCY AND YOUR GRACE.
>> BECAUSE BEING A MAN IN THE
MIDST OF ONLY WOMEN, WHATEVER
THEY CHOOSE TO DO IS GOING TO GO
DOWN.
IF GIHOME BECAUSE THEY WANT ME
TO GO HOME, THERE'S NOTHING I
CAN DO.
>> WE'RE GOING TO ELIMINATE
VYTAS TONIGHT.
BUT THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT,
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS TAKE OUT
THE PERSON THAT WON'T STOP
TALKING.
>> GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
SUCTION.
>> MONICA CAN'T STOP TALKING.
EVERY SINGLE TIME CATCH HER,
SHE'S ALWAYS STRATEGIZING.
WHEN YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
OVER-STRATEGIZING IN FRONT OF
YOUR ALLIANCE, THAT'S WHEN YOU
GET IN TROUBLE, AND I'M ABOUT TO
KICK YOU OUT OF THIS GAME IF YOU
DON'T STOP TALKING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I'D STILL LIKE TO KEEP GIRL
STRONG.
>> UH-HUH.
>> I THINK THE GIRL THING IS
GREAT.
>> I JUST, LIKE-- SOMETIMES
MONICA MAKES ME REALLY WORRIED
AND I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD VOTE
OUT MONICA INSTEAD OF VYTAS.
>> HERE'S MY ONLY THING THAT
SCARES ME ABOUT GETTING RILD OF
HER IS THAT WHAT IF WE GET OVER
THERE AND IT'S ALL GUYS.
GUYS.
WE ALL KNOW WHY IT'S A GOOD IDEA
TO STAY WITH THE PLAN.
LET ALL THE GIRLS STICK TOGETHER
AND GET RID OF THE GUY.
KAT'S ALREADY WANTING TO SWITCH
THAT UP AND SEND MONICA HOME.
KAT'S LOYALTY, I DON'T FEEL
LIKE, IS AS STRONG, AND THAT'S
JUST INFORMATION THAT NEEDS TO
BE THROUGHOUT FOR EVERYBODY TO
KNOW.
>> REALLY?
>> YES.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THE STRA STRATEGY.
SHE SAYS SHE WORRIES ABOUT YOU
STRATEGIZING TOO MUCH.
>> THAT IS A LITTLE WORRISOME,
ESPECIALLY IF WE MADE A PACT
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE OUT VYTAS--
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
IF WE HAD A GIRLS' ALLIANCE AND
SHE'S ALREADY SAYING I WANT
MONICA GONE, HOW DO YOU KNOW
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET TO THE
OTHER SIDE AND SHE SAYS I WANT
TINA GONE.
>> I KNOW.
>> I WAS TOTALLY ON BOARD THAT
IT WOULD BE VYTAS, BUT IF I'M
HEARING THAT KAT'S GUNNING FOR
ME, I NEED TO DO WHAT'S BEST FOR
MONICA.
>> JUST NOW?
>> UH-HUH.
>> WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT IF
WE SHOULD TELL VYTAS THAT HE'S
GETTING ELIMINATED OR NOT.
>> RIGHT.
THERE WASN'T ANYTHING THAT YOU
SAID ABOUT ME?
>> NO, NOT TO TEEN ANNO.
>> NO.
>> I HAVE BEEN TOLD YOU BROUGHT
MY NAME UP.
>> FROM WHO?
>> PEOPLE HAVE SAID YOU HAVE
SAID MY NAME.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> I KNOW MY NAME'S BEEN THROWN
OUT THERE.
I'VE ASKED HER TO TELL ME THE
TRUTH, AND SHE WON'T.
IF SOMEBODY IS GUNNING FOR ME,
WHICH I CAN FEEL IT.
I CAN SENSE IT IN KAT THAT SHE
IS, IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE TO
KEEP THEM AROUND.
>> I WANT TO GO ALL GIRL STRONG.
I DON'T NEED TO CONTINUE TO
COMMUNICATE ABOUT ALLT ALL THE
TIME.
LIKE-- MONICA'S VERY DANGEROUS,
BECAUSE WHEN SHE STRATEGIZES
PEOPLE ACTUALLY MIGHT LISTEN TO
HER.
SO MY BACK'S UP AGAINST THE
WALL.
I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO STAY HERE AND THAT'S IT.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> SO IF VYTAS HAS TO GO HOME
TONIGHT, HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO
GO HOME.
THAT'S HOW THE NATURE OF THE
GAME GOES.
>> YOU KNOW WHO, RIGHT?
>> NOT FOR SURE.
STILLV?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> AS LONG AS IT'S NOT ME.
>> OR NOT ME.
>> I TEACH MY KIDS DO UNTO
OTHERS AS YOU WOULD WANT THIM TO
DO UNTO YOU.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT IN "SURVIVOR
"I FIGURED IT OUT.
IT'S DO UNTO OTHERS BEFORE THEY
DO UNTO YOU.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT KAT?
IF SOMEBODY IS IT GUNNING FOR ME
I'M WRITING HER NAME DOWN.
I'M TRYING TO CORAL AND PERSUADE
EVERYBODY IN THIS TRIBE TO DO
THE SAME THING.
>> I THINK THE BEST THING IS FOR
KAT TO GO.
>> WE HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION
TONIGHT WHO DOES IT MAKE SENSE
TO SEND, CAPT OR VYTAS?
I THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA TO STAY
WITH THE PLAN, WHICH IS TO VOTE
FOR VYTAS.
BUT KAT'S LOYALTY, I'M NOT SO
SURE ABOUT THAT.
WHO SHOULD GO?
HONESTLY, IT IS A COIN TOSS.
IT IS 50-50.
>> Jeff: SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
THE TRIBE SWITCH.
KAT, NEW GROUP OF PEOPLE.
WHO'S NOT GETTING ALONG?
>> I GUESS IT'S JUST BETWEEN
MONICA AND I.
I SAW MONICA WAS KIND OF DOWN,
SO I JUST WENT OVER TO ASK HER
HOW SHE'S DOING.
AND THE CONVERSATION DIDN'T END
UP AS WELL AS I THOUGHT IT
WOULD.
>> Jeff: MONICA WHAT WAS THE
CONVERSATION ABOUT, FROM YOUR
SIDE?
>> JUST ABOUT THE GAME.
AND TRUST ISSUES.
I MEAN, ALL I'M LOOKING FOR IS A
LITTLE BIT OF TRUST.
AND YOU WANT IT SO MUCH FROM
THIS YOUNG LADY BECAUSE I
GENUINELY AM CHEERING FOR HER.
AND IT'S REALLY DIFFICULT.
>> MONICA, THIS SHOULDN'T BE ANY
YOU AND I RIGHT NOW.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> LIKE, I GENUINELY LOVE
MONICA, AND I LOVE THESE GIRLS.
LIKE I ALWAYS HAVE THEIR BACK.
AND IF WE ALL MAKE IT TO THE
MERGE, I FEEL LIKE THAT WE
SHOULD ALWAYS STICK TOGETHER.
NO OFFENSE.
>> Jeff: THAT WILL ONLY HAPPEN
IF TONIGHT VYTAS IS VOTED OUT.
>> JEFF KAT'S GOING TO WRITE MY
NAME DOWN TONIGHT PROBABLY.
AND I FEEL FOR THEIR
RELATIONSHIP, BUT TRUST IN THIS
GAME IS STICKING WITH YOUR
ALLIANCE NO MATTER WHAT.
SO IT'S DIFFICULT TO BE THE ONE
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK WHEN I
FEEL LIKE I HAVE ESTABLISHED
SOME PRETTY GOOD RELATIONSHIPS
AROUND HERE.
>> JEFF, I'VE ESTABLISHED
RELATIONSHIPS HERE.
I HAVE ALL OF THEIR BACKS AND
THEY KNOW IT.
MONICA, YOU KNOW I ALWAYS HAVE
YOUR BACK.
>> OH, KAT.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S NOTHING MORE
THAN I WANT TO DO THAN TRUST YOU
AND I SERVED IT UP ON A SILVER
PLATTER A FEW TIMES TRUSTING.
AND IN THE END, I EVEN HEARD
YOU'VE THROWN MY NAME AROUND.
>> Jeff: KAT, DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING HOME TONIGHT?
>> I HOPE I DON'T.
I WANT TO STAY.
AND YOU GUYS KNOW HOW MUCH I
WANT TO STAY.
PLEASE, BECAUSE I WILL DO
ANYTHING.
>> Jeff: WHO SHOULD BE GOING
HOME?
>> I FEEL LIKE THE WOMEN SHOULD
STICK TOGETHER LIKE OUR PLAN WAS
FROM THE GET-GO, AND VOTE OUT
VYTAS.
>> JEFF, I HEAR A LOT OF "I'M
SORPRY."
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY MADE SOME
MISTAKES IN BUILDING TRUST WITH
HER PARTNERS, BUT I HAVEN'T MADE
ANYONE TO ANYONE HERE--
>> WE WON'T KNOW THAT.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU HAVE
FIVE STRONG GOING INTO THE MERGE
IF ONE PERSON HAS DEMONSTRATED
ALREADY THAT THEY CAN'T BE
TRUSTED.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
AND JUST BECAUSE VYTAS COMES IN
AND HE'S GENUINE TO EVERYBODY
FOR 24 HOURS, WE DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
BUT YOU DO KNOW I WILL STAY
HERE, AND I LOVE THESE PEOPLE,
AND THEY KNOW THAT.
>> Jeff: TINA, ONE SIDE SAYS
STICK WITH YOUR ALLIANCE, DON'T
LET THE OUTSIDERS IN.
THE OTHER SAYS TWO NEW PEOPLE?
CHANCE TO BREAK THINGS UP.
>> YEAH, WELL FOR ME IT'S A
LITTLE BIT DIFFICULT BECAUSE I
HAVE A LOVED ONE OVER HERE NOW.
THAT PUTS A WHOLE NEW DYNAMIC ON
THINGS.
AND SO, I HAVE TO MAKE MY
DECISION BASED ON WHAT I THINK
IS GOING TO GET ME FURTHER
TONIGHT AND POSSIBLY IN THE
FUTURE.
>> Jeff: SO, VYTAS, HOW DO YOU
MAKE SURE IT ISN'T YOU TONIGHT?
>> ALL I CAN REALLY DO IS COME
IN HERE AND JUST BE OPEN, BE A
LITTLE BIT VULNERABLE,UN, SHOW
THE PERSON THEY REALLY AM.
AND THAT'S IT.
THE REST IS LEFT FOR THEM TO
JUDGE AND SAY OKAY, DO WE BUY
THIS GUY?
CAN WE TRUST HIM?
OR DO WE JUST STICK WITH WHAT WE
HAVE?
>> Jeff: KAT, WE'RE JUST GO
BTO VOTE.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE ON YOUR
MIND JAI LOVE YOU GUYS.
FROM DAY ONE I HAVE HAD ALL YOUR
BACKS EXPWI ALWAYS WILL.
>> Jeff: VYTAS YOU'RE SHAKE
YOUR HEAD.
>> I'VE HEARD STORIES ABOUT HER
NOT HAVING PEOPLE'S BACK.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> SHE SOUNDS LIKE SOMEBODY WITH
HER BACK UP AGAINST THE WALL I
GOT CAUGHT THROWING PEOPLE'S
NAMES OUT.
PLEASE, I WILL NEVER DO THAT
AGAIN.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
MONICA, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> I HAVE BEEN THERE.
CAN I PLEASE FINISH.
IT SUCKS TO MAKE MISTAKES.
>> PLEASE STAY TOGETHER, GUYS.
>> AND WE WILL STAY TOGETHER.
AND WE WILL STAY STRONG.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
LAURA B, YOU'RE UP.
>> I HOPE YOU ENJOY THE AMBIANCE
AT REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTE.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, VYTAS.
KAT.
ONE VOTE VYTAS, ONE VOTE KAT.
TWO VOTES KAT, ONE VOTE VYTAS.
KAT.
THAT'S THREE VOTES KAT, ONE VOTE
VYTAS.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR" VIEFER, KAT, YOU NEED
TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
KAT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: WELL, ONE THING IS
CLEAR-- YOU DON'T GET TRUST BY
ASKING FOR IT.
YOU GOTTA EARN IT.
YOU WANT TO WIN THIS GAME AND
YOU HAVEN'T STARTED EARNING
TRUST, YOU BETTER GET TO IT
RIGHT NOW.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
>> MORNING BOO.
>> Jeff: IN A TALE OF TWO
BROTHERS, VYTAS IS QUICKLY
MAKING FRIEND.
>> I WOULD BE HONORED IF HE TOOK
AN INTEREST IN KATIE.
I'M READY FOR GRAND BABIES.
>> Jeff: WHILE ARAS' ARE
ALMOST GONE.
>> WE HAVE TO TAKE OUT ARAS
SOONER THAN LATER.
HAPPY.
>> SOLID.
>> HEY.
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT HAYDEN.
I'M WORRIED HE'S GOING TO BE
DISAPPOINTED IN ME AND GOD
FORBID THIS DOES ANYTHING TO OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
OUR RELATIONSHIP IS JUST
STARTING AND NOW I'M LIKE WHAT
IF I EMBARRASS ALL HIS FRIENDS.
WHO WANTS TO DATE SOMEONE WHO
DOESN'T MAKE THE MERGE?