>> Jeff: LAST TIME ON
"SURVIVOR,G
PLAYERS WERE IN CO THE
GAME.
>> WE ARE DRAW FOR NEW
TRIBES.
SHOOK THINGS UPSURPRISE SWITCH
HAS AS WOMAN ON TADHANA
AND VYTAS AS THE ONLY MAN ON
GALANG.
>> ME AND FIVE GIRLS.
I'M THE ONLY MAN.
>> Jeff: .
>> WAY CUT AWAY THE
ARS ARE A.
>> YOU'RE
DEEPER.
>> HOPEFULLY THE THIS WILL BE
SMALLER ON ME AND LARGER ON
ARAS.
>> AT THE NEWALANG, THE PLAN
WAS OBVIOUS.
>> IT WOULD BE MAYBE VYTAS
BECAUSE HE'S NOT A GIRL.
>> Jeff: TYSON AND ARAS THINK
THEY HAVE IT.
TADHANA WINS IMMUNITY!
BUT PAF GALANG LOST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, CAT TURNING ON
HER ALLIANCE.
>> IAT IS GUNNING FOR ME, I
NEED TO DO WHAT IS BEST FOR
MONICA.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL SHE
MADE ONE FINAL PLEA.
>> MONICA, YOU KNOW I ALWAYS
HAVE YOUR BACK.
>> OH, KAT, THERE'S NOTHING MORE
THAT I WANT TO DO THAN TO TRUST
YOU.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, HER
BETRAYAL WAS TOO MUCH TO
OVERLOOK.
KAT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
11 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> WELL, AT LEAST I DIDN'T CRY.
THAT'S A GOOD CHANGE.
AT TRIBAL I GOT ELIMINATED.
APPARENTLY WE HAD AN ISSUE WITH
TRUST.
MONICA WAS FEELING ON THE OUTS,
SO WAS LAURA AND THAT WAS THE
PLACE FOR VYTAS TO SWOOP IN FOR
THE KILL AND HERE I AM.
HEY!
SORRY.
>> COME OVER HERE, KAT.
TELL US WHAT HAPPENED.
>> WELL, I HAVE AN
OVERSTRATEGIZER, WHICH IS
MONICA, A SOCIAL (BLEEP) WHICH
WAS LAURA, I HAD A WOMAN WHO HAD
A TARGET ON HER BACK FOR BEING A
MILLION DOLLAR PLAYER AND THEN
HER DAUGHTER WHO'S A TAG ALONG
THEN I GOT THE ONE GUY ON AN
ALL-WOMEN'S TRIBE AND THEY ALL
FLIPPED ON ME.
THERE ARE THINGS I WISH I COULD
TAKE BACK BUT I'M NOT OUT YET.
I STILL HAVE A LOT LEFT IN ME
AND I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I
CAN TO MAKE SURE THAT I WIN
HOWEVER MANY DUELS I HAVE THAT
TO TO STAY HERE.
I FEEL LIKE HAYDEN IS GOING TO
BE SO DISAPPOINTED.
NO ONE WANTS TO DATE SOMEONE WHO
DOESN'T MAKE THE MERGE.
HE'S GONNA DUMP ME.
>> OH, COME ON!
>> I DON'T THINK I PLAYED THE
RIGHT WAY.
I WOULDN'T BE HERE IF I DID.
I KNOW I'M NOT OUT OF THE GAME
YET BUT I FEEL LIKE HAYDEN WILL
BE EMBARRASSED THAT I'M HERE AND
I DIDN'T PLAY BETTER OR TRY
HARDER.
HE'S GONNA BE SO UPSET.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO BE ASHAPED
OF ME BECAUSE I REALLY CARE
ABOUT HIM.
AND IT'S JUST BEEN REALLY HARD
WITHOUT HIM.
BECAUSE WE'RE LIKE A TEAM.
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
AND I JUST HOPE THAT I CAN GO
INTO THE DUEL AND I HOPE THAT I
CAN WIN AND HAYDEN WILL BE BY MY
THE SIDE STILL.
A.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
TADHANA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW GALANG TRIBE.
KAT VOTED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE
COMPETITORS FOR TODAY'S DUEL:
JOHN, LAURA M. AND KAT.
>> CAN YOU HUG ME?
COME HUG HE?
(SOBBING)
I'M SO SORRY!
>> IT'S OKAY.
BABE, IT'S OKAY.
>> I'M SO --
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT, IT'S OKAY.
>> Jeff: SO KAT YOU COME IN
AND IMMEDIATELY GRAB HAYDEN AND
SAY "I'M SORRY."
YOU'RE SORRY ABOUT GETTING VOTED
OUT?
>> YEAH, I'M SORRY THAT I GOT
VOTED OUT.
LIKE, OUR PLAN WAS TO PLAY
TOGETHER AND I FEEL LIKE THAT HE
WAS GOING TO BE DISAPPOINTED IN
ME IF I WAS IN THIS ARENA AND I
STILL KIND OF FEEL LIKE I'M KIND
OF LETTING HIM DOWN.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, HOW'S THAT
SIT WITH YOU?
SHE'S WORRIED ABOUT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP AND THAT YOU MIGHT
SEE HER DIFFERENTLY BECAUSE SHE
GOT VOTED OUT.
>> THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
OUR RELATIONSHIP IS GOING TO BE
FINE.
I MEAN, I'M NOT GOING TO VIEW
YOU ANY DIFFERENTLY, YOU KNOW
THAT.
OBVIOUSLY MY RELATIONSHIP WITH
KAT IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN EVEN
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
>> IT IS.
YEAH.
IT IS.
>> Jeff: I WANT TO CHALLENGE
YOU ON THAT.
ONE OF THE OPPORTUNITIES AT
REDEMPTION ISLAND ARENA IS AT
ANY POINT A LOVED ONE CAN TAKE
THE SPOT FOR THE PERSON IN THAT
ARENA WHICH MEANS YOU WOULD BE
TAKING YOURSELF OUT OF THIS GAME
AND SWAPPING SPOTS WITH KAT, PUT
HER BACK IN THE GAME, YOU'D BE
THE ONE FIGHTING FOR YOUR LIFE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> Jeff: HAYDEN, AT ANY POINT
A LOVED ONE CAN TAKE THE SPOT
FOR THE AMERICAN THE ARENA.
YOU GUYS WANT TO TALK THROUGH
THAT OPTION?
>> YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, ARE YOU OKAY OVER THERE?
>> I FEEL LIKE -- I MEAN, I'M IN
A GOOD SPOT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN A GOOD SPOT.
>> I DON'T THINK -- I DON'T
KNOW.
LIKE, YOU KNOW --
>> Jeff: KAT WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO HAVE HAPPEN?
>> I WOULD SWITCH BECAUSE I'M
AFRAID THAT I WON'T DO WELL IN
THIS DUEL.
BECAUSE IT'S A PUZZLE AND I
CAN'T EVEN SPELL.
BUT I WOULD SWITCH.
>> HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK IS
BETTER FOR US LONG TERM?
LIKE, THINK ABOUT US BEING
TOGETHER LONG TERM.
WHO HAS THE BETTER SHOT TO WIN
THE GAME?
>> YOU KNOW YOU DO.
YOU KNOW I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT
THAT.
HE'S SUCH A GOOD PLAYER.
HE'S SUCH A GENUINE, HONORABLE,
AND HE'S -- EVERY TIME SOMEONE
SAYS SOMETHING ABOUT HAYDEN
THERE'S NOT ONE BAD THING
ANYBODY HAS EVER SAID ABOUT HIM.
AND I KNOW THAT HE WOULD DO SO
WELL IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: SO WHEN HAYDEN ASKS
YOU LONG TERM WHAT'S BEST FOR
YOU GUYS IT SOUNDS LIKE WHAT
HE'S SAYING IS "WHO HAS A BETTER
SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME?"
>> IT IS.
YOU KNOW YOU'D DO BETTER THAN
ME.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> Jeff: SO WHAT'S THE DEAL?
>> I'M GONNA -- I'LL PLAY.
I'LL PLAY HERE AND I WANT YOU TO
STAY.
YOU KNOW THAT MEANS SO MUCH TO
ME THAT HE WOULD.
>> Jeff: THAT HE WOULD COME
DOWN.
>> THAT HE WOULD.
BUT I THINK IT MEANS MORE TO HIM
TO STAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SHALL WE GET TO TODAY'S DUEL?
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S DUEL
YOU'LL RELEASE A MACHETE.
YOU'LL USE IT TO CHOP A ROPE
DROPPING THE BAG OF PUZZLE
PIECES.
YOU WILL THEN USE THOSE PIECES
TO BUILD A FIRE PUZZLE.
VERY SIMPLE IN CONCEPT, MUCH
MORE DIFFICULT TO EXECUTE.
FIRST TWO TO FINISH LIVE TO SEE
ANOTHER DAY ON REDEMPTION AND A
SHOT AT GETTING BACK IN THIS
GAME AND A SHOT AT THE MILLION
DOLLARS.
LOSER IS OUT OF THIS GAME FOR
GOOD, THEIR SHOT AT THE MONEY IS
OVER.
IN ADDITION THE WINNER OF THIS
DUEL WILL DECIDE WHO GETS THE
CLUE TO THE LOCATION OF A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
TWO WILL SURVIVE.
ONE WILL BE OUT FOR GOOD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS, WHIP
THROUGH THOSE KNOTS.
YOU WANT TO RELEASE THAT MACHETE
AND USE IT TO CHOP A ROPE.
THAT WILL DROP YOUR PUZZLE
PIECES.
KAT FLYING THROUGH HERS.
>> COME ON, KAT.
>> GOOD JOB, KAT.
>> Jeff: JOHN HAS HIS.
HE STARTS WORKING ON HIS ROPE.
JOHN HAS RELEASED HIS PUZZLE
PIECES.
KAT HAS HER HAS HERMA SHETTY.
LAURA HAS HERS.
LAURA CHOPS HER ROPE.
>> COME ON, KAT!
>> JOHN WITH AN EARLY LEAD.
KAT HAS HER PUZZLE PIECES.
>> STAY CALM.
>> LAURA HAS HER PUZZLE PIECES.
JOHN HAS HIS BAG EMPTIED HE CAN
START WORKING ON WHAT IS GOING
TO BE A VERY DIFFICULT PUZZLE.
LAURA HAS ALL HER PIECES.
>> COME ON, KAT!
MAKE YOUR BAG BIGGER, KAT,
SPREAD IT OUT.
>> Jeff: KAT STRUGGLING JUST
TO GET THE PIECES OUT OF THE
BAG!
LET'S GO!
>> IT'S OKAY, KAT, YOU GOT IT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: THIS IS THE SAME
PUZZLE COCHRAN WON IN THE FINAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
ONCE YOU GET THE CONCEPT THE
PUZZLE WILL BECOME EASIER, YOU
CAN MAKE UP A LOT OF TIME.
>> GOOD JOB, MOM.
>> Jeff: JOHN STARTING TO GET
THE HANG OF IT.
LAURA GETTING THE HANG OF IT.
KAT STILL HAS YET TO PLACE ONE
PIECE.
>> IT'S A BIG PIECE OVER THERE,
KAT, THE LEFT SIDE.
>> THIS ONE?
>> I'M TELLING YOU IT'S A LONG
BIG PIECE, I CAN SEE IT.
>> Jeff: HAYDEN WORKING HARD
TO HELP KAT GET BACK IN THIS.
JOHN MAKING A LOT OF PROGRESS.
HE'S IN THE LEAD.
LAURA JUST LOOKING RIGHT NEXT
DOOR AT JOHN'S PUZZLE.
>> CHEATER.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: CATHYS SHE HAS HER
FIRST PIECE.
JOHN CLEARLY UNDERSTANDS HOW
THIS PUZZLE WORKS.
NOW IT'S JUST A MATTER OF
PUTTING IT TOGETHER.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: KAT PLACES ANOTHER
PIECE.
>> THERE YOU GO, KAT!
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: EVEN WITH LAURA
LOOKING AT JOHN'S PUZZLE SHE'S
HAVING TROUBLE.
KAT WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> COME ON, MOM!
>> Jeff: .
>>> Jeff: JOHN MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS.
JOHN IS WHIPPING THROUGH THIS
PUZZLE!
THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: CAT KAT NOW STARTING
TO GET THE HANG OF IT.
LOOK AT THAT!
KAT COULD QUICKLY BE RIGHT BACK
IN THIS.
>> COME ON, KAT!
>> Jeff: THE ONLY WAY TO
ENSURING YOU STILL HAVE A SHOT
TO GET BACK IN THIS GAME SO TO
FINISH FIRST OR SECOND.
THAT'S IT.
JON STEADIES HIS PUZZLE.
HE'S GOT A LOT OF PIECES IN.
JOHN VERY CLOSE TO FINISHING
THIS PUZZLE.
JOHN PLACES HIS LAST TWO PIECES
IN.
(APPLAUSE)
JOHN HAS SURVIVED.
JOHN WILL LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER
DAY ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> KEEP WORKING, KAT, KEEP
WORKING.
>> Jeff: LAURA IMMEDIATELY
STARTS LOOKING AT JOHN'S PUZZLE.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE KIDDING ME!
>> Jeff: IT'S LAURA AND KAT
AND THE LEAD IS NOT VERY BIG.
KAT HAS WORKED HER WAY INTO
THIS.
>> LOOK AT LAURA'S.
>> IT'S CHEATING!
>> IT'S NOT CHEATING.
SHE'S DOING IT.
>> COME ON, KAT.
>> Jeff: KAT STRUGGLING WITH
THE ETHICS OF IT.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
LOOKING NEXT DOOR.
YOUR GAME; YOUR RULES.
>> THAT PIECE YOU'RE TRYING TO
FIT, KAT, IS SMOOTH.
SMOOTH ON THE OUTSIDE AND IT
CURVES ON THE INSIDE.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: LAURA STILL WITH A
BIT OF A LEAD BUT KAT IS IN
THIS.
>> IT'S A PIECE LIKE THAT WITH A
POINT ON IT.
I'M LOOKING AT LAURA'S.
IT'S SMOOTH.
>> SMOOTH WITH A POINT.
>> Jeff: LAURA STARTING TO
PULL AWAY NOW.
LAURA WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
KAT STARTING TO FALL OUT OF THIS
NOW.
>> COME ON, KAT.
>> Jeff: LAURA WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
>> SMOOTH PIECE WITH A POINT,
CAT.
>> LAURA DOWN TO THREE PIECES
LEFT.
ONCE SHE PLACES THEM SHE STAYS
ALIVE ANOTHER DAY ON REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
LAURA DOWN TO HER LAST PIECE AND
SHE HAS IT.
LAURA STAYS ALIVE TO JOIN JOHN
ON REDEMPTION ISLAND.
KAT IS OUT OF THIS GAME.
>> GOOD JOB.
JON, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: THAT'S FOUR DUELS YOU
ARE SURVIVED.
LAURA, YOU STAY ALIVE.
TWO DUELS IN.
KAT, FOR YOU AFTER 17 DAYS YOUR
TIME OUT HERE IS DONE.
IF YOU WANT TO SAY GOOD-BYE TO
HAYDEN, TAKE A MOMENT.
>> DON'T LEAVE ME, I LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BREAK UP
WITH ME, ARE YOU?
>> Jeff: KAT, YOU CAN GRAB
YOUR STUFF.
TOSS YOUR BUFF IN THE URN ON THE
WAY OUT.
>> LOVE YOU, KAT.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD JOB, KAT.
>> LOVE YOU!
>> HAYDEN, TAKE CARE OF IT.
>> Jeff: JOHN, AS WINNER OF
THE DUEL, YOU GET TO DECIDE, WHO
GETS THE CLUE TO THE IDOL?
>> I'M A CREATURE OF HABIT,
JEFF.
I'LL GIVE IT TO MONICA.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ONCE AGAIN MONICA.
>> NO DISRESPECT, JOHN, I AM SO
FLATTERED AND HONORED THAT YOU
WOULD GIVE IT TO ME BUT I JUST
FEEL LIKE IT'S POISON IN THIS
GAME.
>> IT'S A GIFT, YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT WITH IT.
>> WELL, THANK YOU FOR THE KIND
GESTURE.
>> Jeff: JOHN, LAURA,
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU LIVE TO SEE
ANOTHER DAY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND AND AWAIT YOUR
NEXT KPUTOR AND NEXT DUEL.
>> GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB, GUYS.
AWESOME.
(APPLAUSE)
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS, HEAD
OUT.
>> YEAH, THAT'S TOUGH, DUDE.
>> I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE.
>> I KNOW YOU HAVE.
I FEEL RESPONSIBLE.
IN REDEMPTION I COULD TRADE
PLACES WITH KAT.
AND I DIDN'T.
BUT AT THE TIME YOU THINK, YEAH,
IT'S THE BEST DECISION.
BUT AS SOON AS I MADE IT I
REGRETTED IT.
YOU FEEL GUILTY OR RESPONSIBLE
BECAUSE, LIKE, KAT IS A LITTLE
NAIVE SOMETIMES AND DOESN'T
ALWAYS KNOW WHICH WAY IS UP.
AND I'M THE ONE THAT, LIKE,
HELPS HER.
I WAS IN A POSITION TO HELP HER
AND I DIDN'T DO IT WHEN I COULD
HAVE.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING I'M PROUD OF,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S WEIRD, BECAUSE, YOU KNOW --
WE ALL KNOW IT'S JUST A GAME BUT
IT'S NOT LIKE -- JUST NOT THAT
EASY.
>> I THINK IT'S WAY HARDER THAN
EVERYBODY THOUGHT IT WAS GOING
TO BE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> GUYS, WE GOT EACH OTHER.
>> SERIOUSLY, LET'S WIN, GO IN
WITH HUGE NUMBERS.
>> I KNOW VYTAS WILL COME WITH
US AND LET'S BALL.
>> WE PULL VYTAS BACK OVER HERE
AND THEN JUST LOCK THEM OUT.
>> LET'S RUN.
>> WITH KAT BEING GONE, YOU FEEL
A LITTLE RELIEF BECAUSE I CAN
PLAY MY GAME.
I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
SOMEBODY ELSE.
I'M ONLY LOOKING OUT FOR ME NOW.
SO I CAN PLAY A LITTLE BIT MORE
CUTTHROAT IF I HAVE TO.
IN FACT, I THINK IT COULD
STRENGTHEN MY RELATIONSHIP WITH
THIS TRIBE BECAUSE THE MAJORITY
OF THE TRIBE OVER HERE, THEY
DON'T HAVE LOVED ONES AND IT'S
KIND OF ONE MORE THING WE ALL
HAVE IN COMMON, EXCEPT ARAS.
>> ANYBODY WANT TO GO OUT FOR A
PEACEFUL WALK AND MEDITATION?
>> I'M GOING TO TRY AND TAKE A
NAP HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE BACK.
>> GOOD LUCK, THOUGH.
>> I COULD HAVEN'T ASKED FOR A
BETTER SITUATION WHEN I CAME
HERE TO HAVE TWO OF THE PEOPLE
THAT I WAS REALLY, REALLY TIGHT
WITH-- SKWRER VAS AND TYSON--
COME ON OVER TO THIS SIDE AND
OBVIOUSLY VYTAS IS MY CORE
PARTNER AT THE END OF THE DAY SO
WHEN WE GET BACK TOGETHER I FEEL
LIKE WE HAVE A DOMINANT POSITION
IN THE GAME.
I JUST NEED TO LET GO, LISTEN,
BE INTUITIVE AND I'LL BE GUIDED
TO THE RIGHT PLACES.
SO EVERYDAY WHEN I MEDITATE I
VISUALIZE JEFF'S VOICE SAYING
"AND THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR:
BLOOD VS. WATER," ARAS.
AND I DO MY BEST TO TRUST THAT
I'M TAKEN CARE OF.
>> YOU GUYS READY FOR THIS?
>> WE'RE GOING TO GO TO THE
MERGE PROBABLY TOMORROW AND I
DON'T KNOW WHOSE NAME YOU HEAR
MOST OUT OF ARAS' MOUTH, MAYBE
YOU CAN GUESS?
>> HIS BROTHER.
>> ALL HE WANTS TO DO IS GET TO
VYTAS, THAT'S A PROBLEM FOR ME.
THEY'VE BEEN THE MOST DANGEROUS
COUPLE IN THE GAME SINCE DAY ONE
AND THEY'RE ONE OF THE ONLY
COUPLES STILL LEFT IN THE GAME.
WE HAVE TO TAKE OUT ARAS OR
VYTAS SOONER THAN LATER.
>> HIS FINAL FOUR HAS TWO SPOTS
TAKEN, HIM AND VYTAS.
>> MERGE IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN SOON.
IF WE STICK TOGETHER WE CAN GET
TO THE END NO PROBLEM.
AND I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW I
WILL STICK WITH ALL YOU GUYS TO
FINAL FIVE 100% MY WORD.
>> I WAS SHOCKED IT WAS TYSON
THAT PROPOSED THE PLAN.
HE SEEMED VERY CLOSE WITH ARAS
BUT ON THE SAME HAND, TYSON'S
SMART.
RIGHT NOW SOMETHING WE HAVE IN
COMMON IS WE KNOW WE CAN TRUST
EACH OTHER IS BECAUSE WE DON'T
HAVE ANYONE OVER THERE WE TRUST
MORE.
>> IS EVERYBODY COOL WITH THAT,
US FIVE AND SMOOTH SAILING?
>> US FIVE.
>> I'M GOOD WITH IT.
>> HAPPY?
>> SOLID.
>> I'M IN.
>> HAPPY?
WE HAVE TO HAVE EACH OTHER'S
BACKS.
>> ARE YOU HAPPY?
>> I'M VERY HAPPY.
I THOUGHT ARAS WAS PLAYING A
GOOD GAME AT FIRST BUT EVERYONE
ELSE IS RECOGNIZING HIS MAIN
MOTIVATION RIGHT NOW WHICH IS
GET TO VYTAS AND THEN TAKE
CONTROL OF THE GAME.
MEDITATE ALL DAY LONG IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU NEED.
I THINK HE'S GETTING COMFORTABLE
AND THAT PLAYS RIGHT INTO MY
GAME PLAN.
MORNING, BOO.
>> GOOD MORNING, PRINCESS.
>> GOOD MORNING TO YOU, TOO.
>> JUST LITTLE LATE
SLEEPER-INNERS.
HOW DID YOU SLEEP?
>> I SLEPT GREAT.
OH, MY GOD, I WAS SO -- JUST
TIRED, YOU KNOW?
>> EVEN THOUGH HE'S NOT PART OF
OUR ALLIANCE I'VE REALLY COME TO
LIKE VYTAS.
HE'S BEEN THROUGH THE SCHOOL OF
HARD KNOCKS AND LOTS OF TIMES
WHEN PEOPLE GET KNOCKED DOWN AND
THEY PICK THEMSELVES BACK UP
THEY'RE A WHOLE NEW PERSON.
>> YOU GUYS LOOK LIKE A LITTLE
HAPPY COUPLE CAMPING ON THE
BEACH.
>> I WOULD BE HONORED IF HE TOOK
AN INTEREST IN KATIE JUST
BECAUSE HE SEEMS LIKE SUCH A
STRAIGHT-UP GUY.
HOWEVER, THE GUY WHO GETS KATIE
IS GONNA HAVE TO HIT HER OVER
THE HEAD WITH A CLUB AND DRAG
HER INTO HIS CAVE BECAUSE KATIE
IS NOT A VERY FLIRTATIOUS GIRL.
BUT ONE CAN DREAM.
I'M READY FOR GRANDBABIES.
(LAUGHS)
WHAT IS THE HARDEST ASPECT OF
THIS GAME FOR YOU?
>> OH, THAT'S EASY.
THE DISHONESTY.
THE TRIBE SWAP WAS TOUGH.
LIKE BEING THE ONE GUY WITH A
BUNCH OF GIRLS.
BUT YOGA HAS TAUGHT ME A LOT
ABOUT DEALING WITH THE FEMININE
ENERGY AND GIRLS AND WOMEN.
SO I KIND OF FEEL LIKE I HAVE AN
IDEA OF WHAT'S GONNA HELP
INGRATIATE ME THE TRIBE MORE.
I'M SUCH A TRUSTING PERSON.
I HAD THIS WOMAN WALK INTO MY
YOGA CLASS BARELY EVEN KNEW,
I'VE SEEN HER A FEW TIMES, SHE
ASKED ME TO BORROW A HUNDRED
BUCKS.
I WAS TAKEN ABACK THAT SHE HAD
THE AUDACITY BUT THEN I THOUGHT
THIS MOMENT OF PRINCIPLE, LIKE I
WANT TO BE T WORLD TO BE A PLACE
WHERE WE CAN JUST TRUST FIRST
AND THEN IF SOMEBODY BREAKS IT,
THEN YOU DON'T TRUST THEM.
SO I GAVE HER THE HUNDRED BUCKS.
I WAS LIKE, SURE.
IN MY EXPERIENCE, WOMEN LOVE A
BAD BOY, BUT WHAT THEY EVEN LIKE
MORE THAN A BAD BOY IS A NEWLY
REFORMED BAD BOY.
SO I'M PUTTING FORWARD THE PARTS
OF ME THAT I WANT THESE WOMEN TO
SEE.
I AM A LIKABLE PERSON, I'M A
TRUSTWORTHY GUY.
IT'S ALL VERY CALCULATED.
BUT IT'S WORKING.
>> WE'RE SO GLAD YOU ARE HERE.
>> ME, TOO.
>> VYTAS, HE'S A WONDERFUL MAN
THAT CAN SHARE HIS EMOTIONS AND
HIS FEELINGS AND I'VE LEARNED A
LOT FROM VYTAS.
JUST BEING MORE OPEN TO PEOPLE.
I'M FEELING LESS GUARDED WITH
THIS SMALL OF A TRIBE AND I FEEL
LIKE I CAN BE MYSELF.
COMING INTO THIS GAME, ONE OF MY
INSECURITIES HAS BEEN MY SOCIAL
GAME.
I WAS RAISED ON A FARM AND I'M
KIND OF A QUIET GIRL THAT'S
SLOWLY COMING OUT OF MICHELLE.
AND I'M BECOMING MORE AT PEACE
WITH WHERE I AM IN THE GAME.
I AM SO GRATEFUL.
I'VE HAD A GREAT TIME.
I'M REALLY TRYING TO ENJOY EVERY
MOMENT.
SO THAT'S WHY I LOVE VYTAS.
BUT I HAVE TO KEEP MY HEART OUT
OF IT BECAUSE HE IS A THREAT AND
I'M WILLING TO STICK WITH THE
GIRLS IF THAT IS WHAT THE
CONSENSUS IS.
I WILL DO WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE
TO FURTHER MY GAME.
>> YAY!
>> LET'S READ IT.
>> CHAINED TO A FAMILY NOT OF
YOUR CHOOSING MAY MAKE YOU A
VICTIM OF FATE.
APATHY OR FATIGUE MAY LEAD TO
YOUR LOSING AND TRIBAL COUNCIL
IS WHERE YOUR CHANGES ABATE.
>> WE'RE ALL CHAINED TOGETHER
DOING SOMETHING.
>> WOW!
>> GOING INTO A PHYSICAL
CHALLENGE WITH TWO WOMEN IN
THEIR 40s, ONE WOMAN IN HER
50s AGAINST A TRIBE OF FIVE
STRONG DUDES AND A GIRL IS
TOUGH.
WE'RE GOING TO BE UNDERDOGS NO
MATTER HOW THE COOKIE CRUMBLES
IN THIS CASE.
I'M NOT GETTING MY HOPES TOO
HIGH.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK IF WE LOSE?
>> THEN IT'S GOING TO BE VYTAS.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER SINCE THE
BEGINNING.
ARE YOU OKAY WITH THAT?
>> NO.
BUT YES.
I MEAN, WE HAVE TO BE.
>> I KNOW, THIS IS THE PART YOU
HATE.
POOR VYTAS.
>> I KNOW, POOR THING.
>> I'M GONNA CRY.
WE JUST HAVE TO WIN.
WE HAVE TO WIN.
>> YES.
>> I DON'T WANT HIM TO GO.
>> I GOT EMOTIONAL THIS MORNING
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, IF WE DO LOSE
VYTAS IS THE ONE GOING HOME.
OUR GIRL ALLIANCE, WE'VE HAD THE
LOYALTY, WE'VE LOOKED EACH OTHER
IN THE EYE, OUR ALLIANCE IS
STILL STRONG.
WE'RE STICKING WITH THAT.
>> WHAT CAN YOU DO?
>> I'M SORRY, GUYS.
>> I DON'T WANT ANYBODY TO GO.
>> LET'S JUST WIN.
>> AND WE DON'T EVEN HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
EVERYBODY READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, CIERA, TAKE
IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, FOUR
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL BE
CHAINED TOGETHER AT THE ANKLES.
TWO OF THOSE PEOPLE WILL HAVE
THEIR WRISTS ATTACHED TO A COIL.
ON GO YOU'LL RELEASE FROM THE
COIL AND MOVING TOGETHER
NAVIGATE THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES COLLECTING BAGS ALONG
THE WAY.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED THE BAGS
THE REMAINING TRIBE MEMBER WILL
USE THE CHAINS AND BALLS INSIDE
TO CREATE BOLOS.
FIRST TRIBE TO LAND THREE BOLOS
ON THEIR TARGET WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
PLAYING?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ALL THE FRIED CHICKEN
--
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: -- YOU CAN EAT.
AN AFTERNOON OF DEEP FRIED
CHICKEN, CORN ON THE COB, MAC
AND CHEESE.
>> A SOUTHERN FEAST.
>> Jeff: ICED TEA, LEMONADE!
WORTH PLAYING?
>> OH, YES.
>> Jeff: TADHANA, YOU HAVE ONE
EXTRA MEMBER, SITTING SOMEBODY
OUT.
YOU CAN SIT OUT WHOEVER YOU
WANT.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SIT OUT?
CIERA, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH,
EVERYBODY ELSE WE'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GOT TO WHIP THOSE THROUGH THOSE
COILS.
>> I'M GOOD!
>> READY?
OUTSIDE, INSIDE.
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES HAVE IT.
NOW YOU'RE MOVING TOGETHER.
TADHANA GOING VERY QUICKLY.
GALANG TAKING THEIR TIME.
THIS IS WHERE IT WILL GET
INTERESTING.
EIGHT PEOPLE CONNECTED AT THE
ANKLES ALL WORKING ON BAGS OF
PUZZLE PIECES TRYING TO STAY OUT
OF EACH OTHER'S WAY AND GET IN
THE OTHER TRIBE'S WAY.
>> I'M GOOD!
LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: ONCE YOU HAVE IT, THE
TRICK IS HOW DO YOU GET OUT
BECAUSE YOU HAVE FOUR OTHER
PEOPLE IN THERE, TOO.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: GALANG HAS ALL FOUR.
THEY'RE TRYING TO HEAD OUT.
TADHANA STILL WORKING ON THEIR
FOURTH.
HAYDEN FINALLY HAS HIS FOURTH.
THEY'RE OUT.
>> STEP, STEP.
OUT.
>> OUTSIDE!
INSIDE!
OUTSIDE!
>> COME ON, GET YOUR OTHER HAND
UP.
>> STEP, STEP, STEP.
>> Jeff: TADHANA ONCE AGAIN IN
FIRST.
GALANG ONCE AGAIN IN LAST!
EIGHT PEOPLE ALL WORKING ON
THEIR BAGS.
>> I'M GOOD!
>> Jeff: ONCE YOU HAVE THEM,
YOU CAN HEAD OUT, YOU JUST GOT
TO GET PAST THE OTHER PEOPLE.
CALEB TRYING TO GET OUT, HE'S
TIED UP BEHIND MONICA.
VYTAS HAS GOT HIS BROTHER ARAS
TIED UP.
MONICA IS BLOCKING ARAS, SHE'S
NOT LETTING HIM THROUGH.
ARAS CANNOT GET THROUGH.
VYTAS HAS HIM TIED UP.
IT'S A MELEE!
ALL KINDS OF ANKLES GETTING TIED
UP IN EACH OTHER.
PEOPLE GOING DOWN.
BUFFS COMING OFF!
BOTH TRIBES HAVE THEIR BAGS.
KNEE HAS THEM, TYSON HAS THEM!
TINA UNTYING FOR GALANG.
TYSON UNTYING FOR TADHANA.
VERY CLOSE.
NOBODY WANTS TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL AND EVERYBODY WANTS
REWARD!
TINA EMPTIES HER LAST BAG, TYSON
STILL WORKING ON HIS LAST BAG.
START ASSEMBLING THOSE BOLOS.
YOU NOW TAKE THE CHAINS AND
CONNECT THEM.
ONE BALL ON EACH SIDE.
ONCE YOU FINISH YOU CAN START
TOSSING THEM.
TYSON AND TINA BOTH WORKING VERY
QUICKLY.
WE ARE NECK IN NECK.
>> COME ON, TY, JUST TWO MORE.
>> Jeff: TYSON HAS ALL THE
BOLOS.
HE'S GOING TO START TOSSING NOW.
YOU HAVE TO LAND THREE.
KNEE CAN START TOSSING.
>> COME ON, TYSON.
>> Jeff: TYSON LANDS HIS FIRST
ONE FOR TADHANA!
TYSON NEEDS TWO MORE.
JUST MISS.
TINA SCORES FOR GALANG!
>> KEEP GOING!
>> Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE COULD
COME DOWN TO SECONDS.
>> COME ON, TYSON, MAKE IT
TIGHT, BABY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TINA.
ATTA BABY!
KEEP GOING!
>> Jeff: TYSON SCORES FOR
TADHANA.
HE NEEDS JUST ONE MORE.
TINA'S GOT TO PICK IT UP.
SHE FALLS SHORT AGAIN IN THE
DIRT.
TYSON CAN DO IT RIGHT HERE!
JUST MISSES.
>> GOT TO GO FAST, MOM.
>> NICE!
ALL RIGHT!
ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: TINA LANDS HER SECOND
FOR GALANG.
IMMUNITY.
FRIED CHICKEN ON THE LINE.
TYSON CAN WIN IT FOR TADHANA
RIGHT HERE.
OH, JUST MISSES!
TINA CAN WIN IT RIGHT HERE FOR
GALANG.
TINA GOES HIGH AND MISSES.
TYSON DOES IT.
TADHANA WINS IMMUNITY AND
REWARD!
>> WHERE YOU AT, GIRL?
>> SWEETIE, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT!
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: TADHANA, STARTED OFF
THIS GAME, COULDN'T WIN, NOW YOU
CAN'T LOSE.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS ONCE AGAIN.
(APPLAUSE)
ALONG WITH A NICE AFTERNOON.
FRIED CHICKEN, BISCUITS, CORN ON
THE COB SET UP FOR YOU JUST
AROUND THE CORNER.
ENJOY YOUR NIGHT FREE OF TRIBAL
COUNCIL AND ENJOY YOUR FOOD.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
LOVE YOU GUYS, GOOD LUCK.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> Jeff: GALANG, TRIBAL
COUNCIL ONCE AGAIN, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT, GRAB YOUR
STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU AT TRIBAL WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT AND SENT TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> DELICIOUS!
AWESOME!
>> PRAYER, BRO.
>> I DON'T HAVE TIME RIGHT NOW.
>> GOD IS GOOD, GOD IS GOOD,
THANK YOU FOR THIS FOOD, AMEN.
>> MACARONI!
>> IT'S A MIRACLE.
>> WE GOT SO LUCKY WITH THE
TRIBE SWAP.
>> WE DID.
>> YOU GUYS DID!
>> YOU GUYS DID SO GOOD.
>> I STARTED OFF THE GAME WITH A
FOUR GAME LOSING STREAK IN
CHALLENGES AND THAT SUCKED AND
NOW WE'RE ON A ROLL.
TADHANA CAN'T BE STOPPED RIGHT
NOW.
I FEEL GREAT AND I'M LOOKING
FORWARD.
THE FUTURE IS BRIGHT.
>> I'M GETTING FULL.
>> I'M NOT.
I WAS BUT I PUSHED PAST IT.
>> WOULD ANYONE BE OFFENDED IF I
TOOK ICE OUT OF THIS LE LEMONAD?
>> DO IT.
WE'RE EQUAL PARTNERS SO YOU CAN
DO IT WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> CAME TO YOUR BEACH AND ATE
YOUR FOOD.
>> I'M A ONE MAN WRECKING BALL.
>IDIDN'T NEED THIS REWARD.
I DON'T THINK I'VE BEEN HUNGRY
ONE NIGHT SINCE WE'VE BEEN HERE.
I'VE CONVINCED EVERYONE EATING
MAXIMUM AMOUNT AMOUNTS OF RICE E
PROPER STRATEGY AND EVERYONE
SEEMS TO JUST AGREE.
I'M A THREE TIME VETERAN OF THIS
GAME SO OF COURSE WHAT I SAY IS
GOING TO BE RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GOING ON
WITH THE OTHER TRIBE?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO'S IN CONTROL
OVER THERE.
THE KAT VOTE BAFFLED ME.
>> I FEEL LIKE VYTAS IS SAFE.
I NEVER KNOW, I THOUGHT KAT WAS
SAFE, TOO.
>> I KNOW WE'RE ALL SAFE.
(LAUGHTER)
>> WELL, HELL.
>> WE ALL TRIED OUR BEST.
WE ALL GAVE IT OUR ALL IN THE
CHALLENGE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> VYTAS, I RESPECT YOU SO MUCH
AND I'VE ALREADY CRIED ABOUT
THIS.
WE'VE DECIDED AS FOUR GIRLS THAT
YOU'RE THE NEXT ONE TO GO.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE I'M -- YOU'RE SUCH A
HUGE THREAT IN THIS GAME.
I MEAN, YOUR BROTHER'S WON
BEFORE.
YOU'RE THE MOST AMAZING MAN.
YOU'RE ONE OF THE MOST AMAZING
MEN I'VE MET.
YOU'VE BROUGHT CALM TO OUR TRIBE
AND I DON'T THINK A BLIND SIDE
IS FAIR AND I DON'T WANT TO --
WE DON'T WANT TO SURPRISE EACH
OTHER AND I THINK IT'S JUST --
LET'S HAVE A GOOD AFTERNOON
TOGETHER.
>> YOU THINK THAT MAKES ME WANT
TO HAVE A GOOD AFTERNOON?
>> NO, I DON'T MEAN THAT.
I GUESS BE AT PEACE KNOWING?
I DON'T KNOW HOW ELSE -- I'M
SORRY.
>> I APPRECIATE YOU TELLING ME.
>> UNFORTUNATELY SOMEBODY HAS TO
GO HOME.
VYTAS IS THE ODD MAN OUT.
I DON'T THINK BACK STABBING AND
SENDING SOMEONE TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL NOT KNOWING WHAT'S
HAPPENING IS A NICE THING AND IT
WAS JUST EATING ME ALIVE SO IT
JUST CAME OUT.
>> WE FOUR GIRLS, IT'S SOMETHING
WE DECIDED THIS MORNING AND WE
WERE HOPING TO WIN AND NOT HAVE
TO DO THIS.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO WRITE
SOMEBODY'S NAME DOWN ON THAT
PARCHMENT.
>> IT WAS REALLY HARD FOR ME.
BUT I FEEL LIKE I DID TAKE THE
BULL BY THE HORNS BY TAKING MORE
OF A LEADERSHIP POSITION IN THE
TRIBE.
IT MAY PUT A TARGET ON MY BACK
BUT HOPEFULLY I'LL GET RESPECT
OUT OF IT AND THE WOMEN WILL
LOOK UP TO ME A LITTLE.
I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE THE LOYALTY
HERE.
>> I HOPE IT STICKS.
>> OH, MY HEAVENS!
SERIOUSLY!
THAT IS THE "SURVIVOR" MOMENT OF
ALL -- TIME!
>> I'M FLABBE FLABBERGASTED!
I MEAN "SURVIVOR" 101, DON'T YOU
MEET WITH YOUR ALLIANCE BEFORE
YOU MAKE AN EXECUTIVE DECISION
TO JUST TELL SOMEONE THEY'RE
GOING HOME?
THE GOLDEN RULE OF "SURVIVOR" IS
TRUST.
IS IT OR IS IT NOT?
I FELT BLINDSIDED!
>> I KNOW!
>> Jeff.
>> THIS MORNING I FELT LIKE I
COULD TRUST LAURA B. BUT NOW I
DON'T KNOW.
BLIND SIDES ARE TERRIBLE AND
I'VE BEEN A VICTIM OF ONE, TOO,
BUT THIS GAME IS BUILT ON TRUST.
>> WE GOT RID OF KAT BECAUSE SHE
WAS DOING THAT.
>> THE PLAN WAS TO VOTE OUT
VYTAS.
WE'RE GETTING DOWN TO THE NUT
CRACKING, SO TO SPEAK, WHAT WE
SAY IN THE HILLS.
AND HE'S THE THREAT.
JUST BECAUSE EVERYBODY SEEMS TO
LIKE HIM.
HOWEVER LAURA B. IS
UNPREDICTABLE AND THAT MAKES ME
NERVOUS.
>> IS IT MY TIME TO GO TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
I THINK IT COULD BE LAURA B.
>> THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
I TRUST YOU GIRLS 100%.
WHEN LAURA B. TOLD ME IT WAS MY
TIME TO GO TONIGHT FOR A MOMENT
I WAS LIKE "I'M SCREWED."
BUT TINA, SHE WAS TELLING ME
THAT LAURA'S GOING HOME.
IT'S GONNA BE A LITTLE
EMBARRASSING FOR HER.
>> IT WOULD BE SUPER EASY FOR
THEM TO WRITE MY NAME DOWN ON
THE PARCHMENT BUT I FEEL LIKE
I'VE DONE MY DUE DILIGENCE WHEN
IT COMES TO BUILDING TRUST WITH
THESE WOMEN SO IT'S NOT GONNA BE
ME TONIGHT.
>> I SHOULD TKPWOPBLT OFF WITH
ANY OF YOU BECAUSE THEN SHE'LL
BE LIKE "WHY ARE YOU TALKING TO
VYTAS?"
AND IF SHE DOES ASK YOU JUST
LIKE SAY HE WAS SAYING HIS
GOOD-BYE.
IT'S LIKE A PRIDE ALLIANCE
FEMALES IN CONTROL BUT THEY
ALWAYS NEED ONE ALPHA MALE TO
KEEP AROUND OTHERWISE THERE'S NO
FUTURE FOR THE PRIDE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
THAT'S MY BIG DILEMMA.
THERE'S PREPAR CUSHIONS BOTH
WAYS.
TONIGHT.
>> TONIGHT WE HAVE TO MAKE A
TOUGH DECISION.
IN MY HEAD I THINK IT'S SMART IF
WE GET RID OF VYTAS BECAUSE AT
SOME POINT YOU HAVE TO THINK
LONG TERM AND IF HE MAKES IT TO
THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL IT
WOULD BE DIFFICULT TO BEAT HIM.
>> OF COURSE THERE'S A LITTLE
FEAR BUT I TRUST YOU GUYS.
>> YEAH.
AT THE SAME TIME, LAURA B. IS
THE WILD CARD.
SHE MAKES THESE DECISIONS
WITHOUT CONSULTING ANYONE AND TO
KEEP SOMEONE LIKE THAT, THAT
COULD HIT THE FAN AND EXPLODE
BACK IN MY FACE.
>> THANK YOU FOR LAURA B. AND
HER STRENGTH AS A NEW PERSON AND
HAVING SO MANY LESSONS TO LEARN
AND THANK YOU FOR VYTAS'
WONDERFUL SPIRIT WHO BRINGS SO
MUCH TO THIS CAMP AS WELL.
>> SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN BUT WHATEVER GOES DOWN
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE PRETTY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO
LAURA
B. AFTER THE CHALLENGE WHAT
HAPPENED WHEN YOU GOT BACK TO
CAMP?
>> WELL, IT IS OBVIOUS THAT WE
ARE FOUR GIRLS AND VYTAS ONE MAN
SO I TOOK IT UPON MYSELF TO LET
HIM KNOW THAT HE WAS THE ONE
THAT WAS GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: WOW.
VYTAS, SO WHAT IS YOUR REACTION?
SOMEBODY TELLS YOU "IT'S YOU"?
>> IT WAS DISCOURAGING TO SAY
THE LEAST.
I'VE COME INTO THIS TRIBE AND
I'VE BEEN NOTHING BUT
TRUSTWORTHY AND I'VE BEEN
GENUINE WITH THESE PEOPLE.
TO GET THAT KIND OF NEWS, IT
DIDN'T FEEL GOOD.
>> Jeff: MONICA, TELLING
PEOPLE THEY'RE GOING HOME AS
PLEASANT AS IT SOUNDS IS REALLY
RISKY.
>> I THINK IT'S EXTREMELY RISKY.
SO IF YOU'RE IN AN ALLIANCE WITH
PEOPLE BEFORE YOU BLOW THE COVER
WE MIGHT WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT
FIRST.
>> Jeff: KATIE, WHERE DO YOU
WEIGH IN ON THAT?
BECAUSE LAURA B. IS SPEAKING FOR
THE GROUP WHICH COULD
POTENTIALLY IMPACT YOU.
>> I AGREE WITH MONICA.
IF YOU'RE IN AN ALLIANCE YOU
SHOULD DISCUSS THESE THINGS SO
WE WERE TAKEN AWACK.
I WISH WE COULD HAVE TALKED
ABOUT IT BEFORE.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, IT SEEMS LIKE
WE'VE NARROWED IT DOWN TO YOU'RE
GOING UNLESS YOU CAN CONVINCE
THESE WOMEN THAT SOMEONE ELSE
SHOULD GO AND IT SOUNDS LIKE
THAT COULD BE LAURA B. BECAUSE
SHE SPOKE UP TRYING TO DO THE
HONORABLE THING IN A GAME THAT
IS ANYTHING BUT HONORABLE.
>> YOU KNOW, THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL KAT WENT HOME BECAUSE
SHE WASN'T TRUSTWORTHY.
I MEAN, I DIDN'T PITCH ANYBODY
SPECIFICALLY.
I'VE BEEN A GREAT MEMBER OF
GALANG AND IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW
MANY GIRLS YOU HAVE, IT MATTERS
HOW MANY TRUSTWORTHY PEOPLE YOU
HAVE.
>> Jeff: TINA, IT'S A DECENT
ARGUMENT FROM A GUY WHO HAS
NOTHING TO LOSE BECAUSE HE'S ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK TONIGHT.
>> IT'S TRUE AND VYTAS IS SO
MUCH LIKE HIS BROTHER.
THEIR HONESTY AND SINCERITY,
THEY REEK OF IT.
NOW, COULD THEY BE FOOLING YOU?
ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
BUT IF YOU WERE GOING ON
INSTINCT, THAT'S WHAT YOU WOULD
FEEL.
>> Jeff: VYTAS, IF IT'S YOU
TONIGHT, WHAT'S YOUR STORY?
>> I MEAN, I WAS IN A POSITION
WHERE I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO
MOVE FORWARD REALLY WELL, THEN
THERE WAS A TRIBE SWAP, I WAS
THE ONE GUY WITH FIVE GIRLS AND
IF I GO TONIGHT IT'S UNFORTUNATE
BECAUSE I THINK WE CAN MOVE
FORWARD TOGETHER PRETTY WELL.
THAT WOULD BE MY STORY.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOUR BROTHER WILL THINK?
WILL HE BE PROUD OF YOU OR HAPPY
YOU'RE GONE?
>> I THINK ARAS WOULD BE PROUD
OF ME AND I THINK ARAS WOULD BE
PRETTY BUMMED I'M GONE.
OUR RELATIONSHIP HAS SUFFERED
OVER THE YEARS AND THERE'S A FEW
MORE STEPS THAT WE NEED TO GROW
THAT MUCH CLOSER TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: LAURA B. IS, THAT
PART OF VYTAS' APPEAL THAT HE
AND HIS BROTHER HAVE THEIR OWN
UNIQUE STORY?
>> YES, THAT'S PART OF THE
REASON THAT I WANTED TO VOTE FOR
VYTAS BECAUSE THEY DO HAVE SUCH
A BOND.
ARAS HAS WON BEFORE.
THEY'RE A HUGE THREAT IN THIS
GAME.
>> Jeff: WHAT ABOUT YOU,
LAURA?
IF IT'S YOU TONIGHT, WHAT'S YOUR
STORY?
>> I TRIED TO BE MYSELF AND PUT
MYSELF OUT THERE, LET MY GUARD
DOWN.
>> Jeff: SO THAT SOMETHING
YOU'RE LEARNING OUT HERE?
>> YES.
I WAS RAISED IN A QUIET FAMILY
AND KEEP TO YOURSELF SO I
STRUGGLE WITH LETTING PEOPLE
KNOW WHO I AM AND IT'S BEEN HARD
FOR ME.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOUR HUSBAND RUPERT WILL MAKE OF
THE WAY YOU PLAYED THE GAME?
>> I THINK NO MATTER WHAT RUPERT
WOULD BE PROUD OF ME.
I'VE BEEN IN RUPERT'S SHADOW FOR
A WHILE AND IT FEELS GOOD JUST
TO BE OUT HERE FOR MYSELF AND I
FEEL LIKE I'M COMING INTO MY OWN
AND IT FEELS GOOD.
>> Jeff: TINA, TOUGH DECISION.
YOU HAVE VYTAS WHO'S TELLING YOU
"LOOK, I'M TRYING TO BOND WITH
MY BROTHER."
YOU HAVE LAURA B. SAYING "I HAVE
BROKEN OUT OF MICHELLE AND PUT
MYSELF IN A VULNERABLE SPOT WITH
YOU PEOPLE."
>> IT'S HORRIBLE.
SOME PEOPLE DON'T COME HERE TO
MAKE FRIENDS.
BUT THAT'S MY GOAL.
I DO LIKE HEARING THE STORIES.
THAT'S PART OF THE JOY THAT I
TAKE AWAY FROM THE HARD, HARD
GAME.
>> I'VE GOT TO SAY, JEFF,
EVERYBODY HERE HAS AN AMAZING
STORY.
THESE ARE AMAZING UNIQUE PEOPLE
WITH GREAT STORIES BUT WHEN I
MAKE MY VOTE IT'S WHO DO I THINK
IS THE LEAST TRUSTWORTHY.
WE SHOULD BE JUDGED ON OUR
MERITS OF THE PRESENT, NOT OF
OUR PAST AND HOW WE'VE PLAYED
THESE LAST 18 DAYS SO FAR.
THAT'S IT.
JUST THAT SIMPLE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
LAURA B., YOU'RE UP.
>> THAT WAS A SWEET SPEECH YOU
GAVE TO ME AT CAMP TODAY.
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN SWITCHED
AROUND THE OTHER WAY, THOUGH.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE: VYTAS.
LAURA B.
ONE VOTE VYTAS; ONE VOTE LAURA
B.
LAURA.
THAT'S TWO VOTES LAURA; ONE VOTE
VYTAS.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VS. WATER,"
LAURA, THAT'S THREE, THAT'S
ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
LAURA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE, GUYS.
>> Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL ILLUSTRATES ONE OF THE
TRICKIEST PARTS OF THIS GAME:
EVERY TIME YOU OPEN YOUR MOUTH
YOU RISK SAYING SOMETHING THAT
CAN GET YOU VOTED OUT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
"SURVIVOR" -- THE WINNER OF
TODAY'S DUEL WILL REENTER THIS
GAME.
SOMEONE'S COMING BACK FROM
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
WHO'S GOING TO HOLD OUT THE
LONGEST?
>> I AM NOT LETTING GO!
>> Jeff: AND WHAT WILL HAPPEN?
DROP YOUR BUFFS, WE MERGED.
BLOOD FINALLY MIXES WITH WATER.
>>> HEY, GUYS.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
THEY'RE KEEPING VYTAS.
AND THEY VOTED ME OUT.
THEY DIDN'T GO WITH THE PLAN
THAT I THOUGHT WE WERE DOING SO
HERE I AM.
>> I WAS PRETTY SURE IT WAS
GOING TO BE VYTAS, TOO.
>> I KNOW.
IF I GO BACK IN THE GAME I'M
CERTAINLY NOT SIDING WITH THE
GIRLS AND THAT IS FOR DAMN SURE.