translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
- He's an immunity idol.
- I'd like to give it to LJ.
I would like to protect
Tony's back.
He is also
an immunity idol.
After LJ and Tony sacrifice
their idols for each other...
- Who betrayed?
- Kass.
...and that Kass betrayed...
zero chance of winning the game.
...power passed to a
new majority alliance of six,
led by LJ and Tony.
It's us six against them four.
In numerical terms,
my alliance dominates.
The numerical hierarchy
being established,
everyone concentrated
on finding idols.
Anyone looking here?!
There is an idol
with special powers near the camp.
Luckily for Spencer,
he found one.
But it wasn't
the one with the special powers.
He's a simple idol, but
I potentially bought some time.
And in the immunity test,
he lasted longer than the others.
Spencer wins immunity
and is protected at tonight's council!
Approaching the board,
the majority alliance
feared the presence of an idol.
Look at Morgan!
She just sleeps.
If they have an idol,
they will not share it with her.
She must go.
And on the board...
Four Tony votes, five Morgan votes,
one vote left.
...they stuck to the safe vote.
Morgan, bring me your torch.
Morgan, the tribe has spoken.
There are nine left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
How is that a compliment,
that you were trying to eliminate me
twice in a row?
- Because...
- Do me a favor.
- ...you're a big threat.
- I appreciate.
Do you know why
we eliminated Morgan?
She didn't deserve to stay.
That's why Jeremiah
and Tash stayed.
Because she doesn't deserve to
play this game.
Twice in a row,
you try to eliminate me.
Me who gets high all the time.
- We want a chance.
- Tell me that's a compliment.
When Jeff turned over
this parchment marked "Tony",
I
probably got over it.
I did not expect that.
I am a 40 year old bald man.
There's Woo, clearly
more athletic than me.
There is LJ, younger
and more athletic than me.
How am I threatening,
why do they want to eliminate me?
We knew that with four votes,
we wouldn't get you out.
You could have
offered it to us too.
"We would like to eliminate Morgan,
because our votes will be
for nothing anyway."
If you had asked us,
I would have voted Morgan.
Yes, you could have approached us.
We are in the majority,
we don't need your votes.
"Spare me, spare me,
we work hard, let
's eliminate this unnecessary dead weight."
You're right.
But I appreciate the compliment.
Now
we are six against three.
But it's never that simple,
even if there are
three defenseless targets.
I could leave tomorrow.
I'm not going to wait quietly until
there are only six of us left.
It may never happen to me
.
And it clearly won't happen
to some of them.
Didn't you flabbergasted that Tony said
take that as a compliment?
- That they voted for him.
- Yes a bit.
Not easy to manage.
- Handle it.
- Light.
It must have made him a bit paranoid.
Yes, this kind of anxiety...
He pretended to laugh about it,
"it's not good".
Will he go into
"mess up" mode?
In effect.
In this game, many problems
come from paranoia
and impatience.
Tony clearly has
paranoia issues and OCD.
He dwells on a lot of things,
his brain never stops.
But it takes patience.
As long as he doesn't do anything stupid!
I did not sleep.
- Was your mind ruminating?
- Yeah.
My name always comes out.
People start
panicking, lying to each other,
to no longer believe themselves.
To look at LJ
is to look at myself in a mirror.
He is lively, he is always
two or three steps ahead.
So I would like him to go,
but I don't want to be
the bad guy who took out his ally.
We are close,
he trusts me 100%.
I have to trick him into breaking a
promise he made to one of us.
It will be my security.
Not only am I leading the horse
to water, but I'm going to make it drink.
That's my goal at the moment.
I think Woo has the idol.
Well, nobody likes to
break their promises,
but we risk...
If he conceals it...
He has it! He has it!
...so he'll play
it when he thinks he's leaving.
Yeah, and I hope he doesn't
take one of us out now.
Do you want to eliminate it now?
- Damn...
- I know.
You have to keep a cool head.
I tell LJ
I'm afraid Woo has an idol.
But it's wrong.
LJ offers me
to eliminate Woo by surprise.
That's all
I wanted to hear.
"You don't know what he thinks."
He is discreet and sneaky.
It's scarier
than someone like me.
"I'm inside.
He, on the contrary,
thinks of eliminating you
from the beginning, without your knowledge."
"And you know nothing about it."
Pit everyone against LJ.
Survivor - Season 28 Episode 9
Bag of Tricks
Mail!
"A sandbag can provide
revitalizing sensations.
Bounce back into the game
sated and energized."
A day at the spa?
I was just beginning to find myself
really dirty and smelly.
The mail announces
a reward trial.
As a reward, we are pampered,
people become sensitive,
emotions come out,
links can be created.
We can discuss
strategy and scenarios.
It's scary,
and that's why I want to win.
If anyone's gotta
make plans, it'll be me.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today you will be divided
into three teams of three.
At my top, you'll throw
a rope through a ring,
to release sandbags.
You'll throw them as far
as you can through a rope tunnel.
When you have them, all together,
advance to the end,
a teammate will
bounce them on a trampoline,
to land them
in a series of baskets.
The first to place
a bag in each basket
win the reward.
- Want to know what's at stake?
- Yes!
For 23 days,
you have been sleeping on bamboos,
you strain your body
in an unusual way,
and your only form of hygiene
is rinsing in the rain.
Then the winning team will enjoy
a spa at the Survivor.
A real shower,
shampoo, soap.
Then a massage, to
reduce all the pain.
Then, a meal at the spa.
Chicken wraps,
spring rolls,
fresh tropical cocktails.
Just what it takes to rejuvenate
your mind and body
for the last 16 days.
We draw the teams
and we start.
We have our three teams!
Jefra, Trish and LJ.
A regenerative in-game reward .
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Jeremiah, Tasha and LJ
throw the rope,
trying to get her
through this ring.
This will release sandbags.
Jeremiah succeeds on the 2nd try!
Jeremiah, Spencer and Tony
take the lead.
It is also Jeremiah
who will throw the bags.
We have to get it back!
There is a learning phase,
as often!
You have to throw them as far
as possible through the net!
LJ hung the ring!
It frees the sandbags!
LJ, Jefra and Trish
move on to stage two.
Woo, Tasha and Kass bring up
the rear.
That's it for Woo!
And it releases the sandbags!
You have to throw them in the tunnel.
It's good for Jeremiah!
It is now necessary to advance
those who have not passed.
Woo takes the hit.
LJ didn't miss any!
He made up a lot of time
for the Oranges!
Woo still throws.
That's it, go ahead!
Take them through the tunnel.
It takes a lot of teamwork.
The Greens remain in the lead.
The Oranges are right behind.
Jeremiah, Tony and Spencer
have their twenty bags.
Put them in the basket
and start bouncing them!
Tony's in charge.
Woo, Tasha and Kass
are still at the tunnel.
Just like Jefra, LJ and Trish.
Tony sets up a first.
Tony sets up a second.
Tony sets up a third!
Three in a row for Tony.
The Oranges have their twenty bags.
Jefra will make them bounce.
Recovery!
Great lead for the Greens.
The Violets have their twenty bags.
Woo makes them bounce.
Everyone bounces
the bags on the trampoline.
Tony sets up a fourth.
He needs one more,
and that's it!
Tony, Jeremiah and Spencer
win the spa day!
Spencer, Tony and Jeremiah,
great day ahead.
First a good shower.
Then a good massage, then a meal.
Grab your things,
go ahead, enjoy the afternoon.
Trish, Jefra, LJ,
Kass, Woo, Tasha,
I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
Earning a reward
can be crucial.
I'm going to talk to Spencer and Jeremiah
because I want to eliminate LJ.
Call me "opportunist".
If I see an opportunity, I take it.
Coming back from the ordeal,
I imagined myself
receiving manicures and pedicures
with a good chicken wrap,
and a fresh mimosa on top...
But I came back to reality.
I'll probably tend
to the fire for hours,
and eat a plate of white rice.
But it's good to know
that my homie Tony
Go keep an eye
on Spencer and Jeremiah,
and make sure they
don't compromise our plans.
They beat us well.
It's true.
Of course,
we would all have liked that, but...
At least we're still here.
Everyone is depressed
for not having won.
But I don't mind,
although it would have been great.
I'm still here,
and I believe in the covenant of six.
And we all know
we better stick together.
Tony is wickedly anxious
right now.
He worries about the idol,
thinks Woo got it,
wonders whether to eliminate
it soon, or even now.
I'm just trying to calm him down.
- We got plenty of votes, I mean...
- Yeah, why worry?
The fact that Tony got so
many votes on the board
gave him the impression
that we wanted to take him out at all costs.
No matter. Our bond is strong,
my loyalty is his.
I released my idol for him,
we are together until the end.
I trust
he will do what is right.
Three people
have to go first.
If one of them goes
all the way, he wins.
But Tony needs to be appeased.
I will soothe him.
Otherwise, we're screwed.
Tony freaks out, he thinks
Woo might have the idol.
I know how to talk
to Tony, so I said
that I would tell him
that he needs to calm down.
We have to stick to the six,
as we said.
I have a plan for the future,
based on patience.
As long as we stick to the plan,
we're in control.
The six must remain welded,
it's the best case scenario
for the three of us.
- Welcome.
- Can I help myself?
Choose. Vodka and rum.
Rewards are an opportunity
to improve my position.
For now,
the cards are against me.
I'm not in a
strong position, but I'm still here.
I've been in a bad position before,
and I've come back from it.
There's no reason
why I can't come back again.
- You played very well.
- Yeah.
And here is our reward!
I was thrilled
to be associated with Jeremiah,
it's kind
of my right arm at this point.
And Tony, I want to know
how he sees things.
Who knows? It might
get me back in the game.
It feels good!
So you want to talk strategy?
Tell me what you think?
Do you think you are going to
be eliminated one by one?
- I do not know.
- It's never that easy.
It depends on what you think.
It's never that simple,
I'm the first to say it.
Just a question.
- Do you feel comfortable in the game?
- I'm never comfortable.
Something will happen.
You know it.
You just have to hold on
until the time comes.
And when the time comes, I will
approach you, you know that.
But will that time come
when we get there?
I think so.
Basically, here
we are pawns.
Pawns on the chessboard,
which you can use if you want.
Talk to Jeremiah and Spencer,
it allows me another big shot
to reach the top.
They just need
to vote LJ when the time comes.
Then I will return with my allies.
There they are desperate.
When people are desperate,
you think for them.
Whatever I tell them,
they will follow.
If they oppose me,
they seal their fate.
It feels really good.
It's nice!
I had never
done anything like this.
- Well, that's it!
- Yeah, that's it.
We could find an agreement.
I must keep you for
when I take action against my team.
Someone is bound to think
of eliminating me at some point.
"Tony is dangerous.",
they see me like that.
I need you to move forward.
Maybe not now,
but I have to keep you.
Next tip,
I can't eliminate you.
- I like big shots.
- I say.
Tony says he has
Spencer and me covered.
He thinks a lot
and he is fully into the game.
There, I have to believe it a little,
even if I have my doubts.
Maybe he's trying to
reassure us before writing our names.
We are here together by chance,
we drew our places,
and it changes the game. That's how
it changes all the time.
- It's that simple.
- We can help each other.
Honestly, I don't
trust Tony.
Tony plays with a lot of people,
he juggles a lot of balls,
and I'm one of them.
He doesn't know, but I have an idol.
If I'm worried,
I won't hesitate to play it.
But I'm going to tell Tony
that I trust him 100%.
'Cause if he can
take me a little further,
I could find the little detour
that will take me to the end.
- It was great?
- Yeah, that was good.
- Did you eat a lot?
- It was like a picnic.
- It's nice to leave the camp.
- Yes, it was nice.
It is the 25th day.
I am in an alliance of three
against an alliance of six.
You do n't need to be
a qualified accountant like me to do the math.
I have to convince someone
to betray or make a big deal.
I think LJ
is smart enough to realize
that Tony won't take
another big guy to the final.
- Would you be ready to discuss?
- I'm ready to listen.
I have a proposal for you.
And a good one.
If you would like
to meet me discreetly...
Tasha wants to have a chat aside,
I said I'd listen.
But Tony is burning with anxiety
right now.
If I go for a walk with Tasha,
I'm just stoking the fire.
Anyway, I don't see
what it could bring me.
I trust Tony,
I'm still here thanks to him.
As long as we stick
to our plan, we'll be fine.
I invited LJ to meet me
to discuss strategy.
He brought me a rabbit.
If LJ had the guts
to take action,
he could take Jefra, Spencer,
Jeremiah and me, and trap Tony.
But it's clear that Tony
is in control, everyone obeys him.
So if nothing changes,
I'm screwed.
Mail!
I already feel good.
Let's see.
"Purple, blue, yellow and red."
"Like a sunset,
the colors are vivid."
"Bruises could
bruise your ego."
"And being knocked out
could make you livid."
This test is crucial.
LJ is smart, it will be the one
of us who strikes first.
Timing is essential.
Now may be the time to strike.
If LJ doesn't win immunity,
he could be next to go.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all, Spencer,
I'm taking that back.
I let you keep it for me.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
After 25 days, the impact of this game
on your bodies is evident.
Today we will see
what impact it has on your minds.
This test
will use your memory.
I'm going to show you
a series of colored tiles.
You will repeat the sequences to me.
As long as it's fair,
you're still in the game.
If you are wrong,
you are eliminated.
The last person standing
wins immunity,
is protected from the vote, and will have
a one in eight chance of winning.
For the losers, someone
will be eliminated from the board.
We draw the places at
random and we start.
Alright, here we go.
First run.
That's all.
Take your first color.
Place it up and let go.
Everyone says yellow.
Everyone is right.
Next color.
Release everyone.
Everyone says blue, except Trish.
Trish, you're either the winner
or the first to be eliminated.
- In your opinion?
- I'm the first eliminated.
- In effect.
- Damn.
Blue was the right color.
Trish got it wrong.
Take a seat on the bench.
Next color.
Let go.
Everyone says red except Woo.
Green is incorrect,
the correct answer was red.
Woo is eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
It's hard to think.
Last color.
Let go.
Everyone says green.
Everyone is right.
Everyone stays in the game.
Next round. Release
your colors, we start again.
Alright, here we go. Next round.
Vert.
Bleu.
Fine, let's go.
Drop your first color.
Everyone says red,
it starts well.
Drop the next color.
Everyone says green.
Again, everyone is right.
Next color.
Everyone says purple.
Everyone is still right.
Next color.
Everyone says black.
Everyone is right.
Next color.
Blue, that's right,
everyone is right.
Next color.
A children's game can be so hard
after 25 days of deprivation.
Let go.
LJ, Tasha and Tony said green.
Jefra, Kass and Spencer
said yellow.
The right answer...
Jefra, Kass, Spencer
and Jeremiah got it wrong.
Take a seat on the bench.
There are only three left.
LJ, Tasha and Tony.
Significant immunity at stake.
Last color.
Let go.
Three different colors.
LJ says red, Tasha says blue,
Tony says yellow.
Tony, you shake your head.
I believe it was red.
- Do you think you were wrong?
- Yes.
It's not yellow.
Lower it, you're out.
Take a seat on the bench.
Only LJ remains in red
and Tasha in blue.
- Are you confident, LJ?
- Rather yes.
- And you, Tasha?
- Me too.
One is right, the other is wrong.
The correct answer is...
LJ was wrong.
Tasha gains immunity.
Congratulation.
Tasha, come here!
Well done, Tash.
It couldn't have been
better for you.
In effect.
Tasha is protected
from voting tonight.
You people,
someone's going away tonight.
Take your things, return
to camp. We'll see you at the council.
Congratulation.
When Tasha won, I
immediately started thinking.
Tonight, we just have to split the vote,
3-3, between Spencer and Jeremiah.
If everyone sticks to the plan,
one of them will leave.
Well done, Tash.
It was hard. I missed the blue.
I'm so excited.
This ordeal was vital for me.
I had a one in three chance
of leaving tonight.
This pretty thing
assures me three more days.
So...
Good for you, LJ!
Split the votes.
Why? Because of an idol?
Yes. We stay strong,
but if someone betrays...
No one is going to cheat at this point.
Well, I hope.
So it's not
the best strategy.
I feel safe
for the first time.
We have the majority, Spencer
and Jeremiah are easy targets.
But Tony worries
that Woo has an idol,
he thinks
maybe we should take care of it.
Which is really stupid.
We made a plan,
we all swore to stick to it.
That's what we have to do.
Who votes who?
The girls vote for Jeremiah,
the boys for Spencer.
I won't wait
to get hit by LJ.
He said he was ready to eliminate Woo.
It's true, I tricked him a bit.
But I don't care.
I'll pass LJ off
as the main agitator.
That's what I have to do.
LJ is dangerous.
I have to knock now,
before he had the idea
to attack me.
But first,
I have a lot of work.
We're OK, huh?
I do not know.
LJ is shady.
He wants to kill you, but I don't.
If he betrays his promise to you,
he will do the same to me.
It's ridiculous.
I was all in with all six,
but apparently LJ, that hustler,
for some reason,
wants to eliminate me.
If he approaches Tony,
my closest ally,
and said "Woo has to go",
we may have
to take action before him.
He is ready to burn you.
So you want
to create the surprise again?
Yeah, that's fine with me.
I trust Tony,
he protects me.
It's great
that he's on my side.
If all goes well, this will
still be one hell of a piece of advice.
This is what will happen.
We're gonna start killing each other.
LJ wants to eliminate Woo.
He goes back on his promise.
It's bad.
Please
trust me, Spencer.
Otherwise, it's all screwed up.
You are 100% safe.
Initially, Tony wanted to save
Jeremiah and me for later.
But apparently
LJ is conspiring to take out Woo.
So Tony wants
to take action now.
I'm in trouble
because I'm causing trouble.
It's going to be
like a bomb.
Make
sure Jeremiah is in.
Shall we talk to Tasha about it?
OK.
I'm glad it's Christmas!
When I woke up, I thought I would find
only ashes under the tree,
but there's this giveaway called
"let's eliminate LJ".
It sounds too good
to be true.
It could be a canard
for me not to play my idol.
But I'll take
whatever they give me.
'Cause if I can go
just a little further,
having a few votes with me
is a whole new game.
Right now,
Tony is probably aiming for LJ.
- You are in?
- I'm with you, and we'll be with him.
You do not have to worry.
When I arrived in this tribe,
I had nothing.
You have to be careful, he's smart.
Yes, it is very dangerous.
But for now,
let them kill each other!
When I was on reward,
what did you talk about?
LJ was concerned about
your worries about Woo.
He was the one who was worried,
he wanted to eliminate her.
I told him we had a deal.
He told me that it was you
who wanted to eliminate him.
I know you like him,
but he's a sneak.
He told me that you find Woo
dangerous, that you panic
and wanted to eliminate him, but
thought it was a bad idea.
But no. He is lying to you.
What do you think he wants,
to finish fourth?
It's you, me and Woo.
Us three against Jefra and LJ.
Do you think he doesn't think about it?
He is already anticipating the sequel.
You do not understand?
So what do you suggest?
Nothing yet.
Tony gets really paranoid.
He told me that LJ was trying
to pop the six.
But LJ told me
something completely different.
"God, Tony is totally freaking out."
"He wants out Woo."
I don't know what to believe.
Let's say you, me and Woo
write LJ's name.
And I would tell Tash, Spencer
and Jeremiah to do the same.
I think we should
stick with the six, right?
Yeah, but I do
n't trust LJ anymore.
Why do you think
he told me yesterday
that you wanted to eliminate Woo?
I do not know. It's a trick.
I do not think so.
Trish, you don't realize.
LJ could be up to something.
He's probably up to a lot of stuff.
He wants to win.
But Tony has already played me.
And I'm gullible. But not stupid.
So there's no way
I'm betraying the six.
We're all OK, huh?
It's certain?
- When Tony saw his name four times...
- He was pissed.
Yeah, and I don't think
he's gonna let it go.
I said "Relax!".
No one has any interest
in screwing everything up now.
Nothing like a surprise elimination , but it's too soon.
No one has an interest in acting
now. It would be stupid.
I think Tony knows that.
The six of us have a great position,
as long as we stay together.
- Do you think he will?
- I do not know.
It's 50-50.
I have a big plan in action.
But Trish wants
the six to stick together.
So if I eliminate LJ,
there will be resentment.
Trish has been with me since the beginning,
she's my closest ally.
If I do that, she could
turn against me.
And all of this could
blow me in the face.
If so, I'll have
to stick to my covenant.
I would prefer to act now.
But in life
as in Survivor,
you have to know when to lick
asses and when to kick them.
Unfortunately, tonight I risk
having to lick asses,
and eliminate
Spencer or Jeremiah.
Now here are
the members of the jury.
Sarah, and Morgan,
eliminated at the last council.
Jeremiah, unless
something drastically changed,
it looks like you, Tasha
and Spencer are always in trouble,
and that the other six
are still welded.
Yes, those six are solid.
Spencer and I
look at each other and say:
"Damn, that doesn't smell good.".
Kass, you have a lot to do
with this division.
Do you have empathy
for your three ex-allies?
It's the game, Jeff.
Others may do
the same kind of shots as me.
You can't play this game
without getting your hands a little dirty.
Tony, Kass says get
your hands a little dirty in this game.
That's right, Jeff.
Everything is confused. We don't know
who is saying what, who is telling the truth.
By coming into this game,
we accept the idea
that we are going to be deceived,
that we are going to be betrayed.
Which is why I brought
my bag of tricks today.
- What's in it?
- We'll probably find out tonight.
But it helps
me feel comfortable.
Tasha, that's exactly
what you want to hear.
If all six are welded,
why does Tony say:
"I brought my bag of tricks,
we will surely see tonight"?
That's why I'm happy
to wear this lovely necklace.
'Cause the alliances seem solid,
but the more time we spend in them,
the more cracks one can see
in these "solid alliances".
LJ, Tasha describes your alliance
with quotation marks.
I think she's just
snapped back to reality,
and that she just hopes there's
a crack in our alliance.
Have you been approached by Spencer,
Tash or Jeremiah today,
looking for this crack?
Vaguely, yes.
But I took a step back
and realized
that there was no reason
to create anxiety in the group.
We are really tight.
In your profession, LJ,
how important is loyalty?
Huge. But it's a
very hard thing to find.
Do you think you are a good judge of it?
Yes, I think I have a nose
for disloyalty.
I think I am a good judge of it.
- Tony, what's your job?
- Building.
Does loyalty play a role here?
Yes, we have already seen that 100 times.
You turn your back,
one of your tools disappears.
Trust
is hard to establish.
Especially in Survivor.
Kass, does loyalty
play a role for you?
At home, yes.
But I tried to leave
my life behind when I got here.
You have to be purely selfish
to get far in this game.
It's Survivor, not life.
It's hard to separate things.
But that's the beauty of the game.
We are constantly torn between
being a person and being a player.
Can we be both?
Woo, if loyalty
is very important,
when do you come to say:
"There are threats in my alliance,
I must eliminate them."?
At this point, it's normal for
everyone to be a bit paranoid.
But we six, we stay strong,
and it is in our interest to eliminate
the three outsiders.
But the time will come
when we have to take action.
Spencer, do you think you know
who is sixth among them?
No, I don't know
who is last.
But someone is.
And if we tell you "we are solid,
there is no crack",
you may be the last.
It's time for people to think
about how to position themselves to win.
Trish, a part of you
she thinks
that if someone is last,
it's time to act?
I think this "happy family"
will quickly malfunction.
I reassured myself by saying to myself:
"there are six of us and three of them".
But suddenly, we say to ourselves:
"It doesn't stop there,
it's only the beginning".
A rupture must occur,
it is what I anticipate.
It will happen.
- When?
Tonight, maybe,
but if so, I don't know.
But with every tip,
things get crazy, so...
It's very fun, and at the same time
it puts the ball in the stomach.
Well, it's time to vote.
Woo, it's up to you.
Fingers crossed
for another
surprise elimination in Cagayan.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote...
LJ.
Three LJ votes.
Jeremiah.
Three Jeremiah votes,
three LJ votes.
spencer.
A Spencer vote.
LJ.
Four LJ votes, three Jeremiah votes,
one Spencer vote, one vote left.
Ninth person eliminated
and third member of the jury...
LJ. Bring me your torch.
Good game.
LJ, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Good luck.
Did you change sides?
This vote,
and the reactions it provokes,
once again proves that
Survivor is an individual game.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
Today, I am on a mission.
Tony will stop at nothing
to stay one step ahead.
Sorry, I don't want
to be fooled by Tony.
My God, look at this!
Let me try to climb it.
And Woo's food mission
turns tragic.
Yeah, go!
I was taken by surprise.
It's hard to find the balance
between patience and confidence.
Acting too soon
can backfire.
But if we wait too long,
we can meet again
to wonder where we went wrong.