translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Solidarity of the "blues"!
Two policemen, Tony and Sarah,
made an alliance pact.
He knows that I will be loyal to him,
and vice versa.
But a surprise change...
Throw away your bandanas.
...separated them.
I am the only
original Aparri in the tribe,
with three members of Intelligence
and three of Beauty.
While the division was clear
in Sarah's new tribe,
Tony's New Tribe
had everything
Survivor can offer.
Two idols...
I keep it to myself
until I play it.
...a surprise elimination...
...and they even saw
one of them give up.
Lindsey retires from the game.
She was the body and Cliff the head.
Two for the price of one.
But despite everything,
they won the last immunity.
Solana wins immunity!
The top five, baby!
On the board, the new Aparri
was focused on a possible merger.
If you want to go all the way,
and you anticipate a merger,
your group must be united.
At the merge, Jeremiah or Alexis
could join the other side.
Eventually, everyone felt
that Alexis was more likely to betray.
Alexis, the tribe has spoken.
There are eleven left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
- Alexis was crying?
- Yes.
- Really?
I felt great after
the counseling. My game has improved.
We can get there.
We are a good team.
Now everyone
walks with the six.
A merger tomorrow would be
the best news for us.
Because we control the game.
There are six of us and five of them.
In case a fusion
happens as soon as we wake up,
we must choose
our first two eliminated.
- So who first?
- Random, Trish.
Or Jefra. Everyone has to be considered
.
Everyone understood.
- Oh yeah.
- It's all good.
We are the top six, 100%.
- It's in our hands.
- As long as no one betrays.
The top six!
This group is supposed to be
six tight-knit people.
If we can stick together,
we can control the game,
and take out a less obvious target,
like Trish or Jefra.
Top six. That's not cool?
Much cooler than the top five!
It seems so simple.
But merging often shatters
the best plans.
Last night
brought everyone together.
The main thing is to remain silent.
That they have no idea
who is leaving.
The only ones I could
worry about are Jeremiah and you.
It could get out of hand here.
Trust me, I'm not going anywhere.
That she accuses me of not
keeping my word, it clicked.
No one likes
to be called a liar
and basically she called me
a liar, without saying so.
I did nothing to make
you doubt my trust.
I don't think you're going to cheat.
- That would be silly.
- I won't.
- That's why it hurts me.
- I did not want to hurt you.
What more do I need to do
to prove my loyalty to you?
This is where it will break.
If you don't trust
me and I feel it.
If it seems to me that you think I'm
hesitating, that will drive me away.
People think that a betrayal
will cause the loss of this tribe.
But the loss will come
from lack of confidence.
That will be it, and that will be our end.
I refuse to pass
for a liar.
So let's shake hands,
that's how I do.
Me too. Let's shake hands.
I am with you.
- You're with me?
- I am with you.
Very well.
No more talking about it.
In my work,
we need proof.
Just because you voted
with us once doesn't mean I believe you.
There are eleven people left,
eight have to leave, right?
You did what you had to do,
from my point of view.
Not out of loyalty, but out of desperation,
because it was the right thing to do.
You haven't proven anything to me,
except that you're protecting yourself.
Show me an ex-
teammate's blood on your hands and we'll talk.
Survivor Season 28 Episode 7
Serpent's Head
Hello Solana!
- Hello, the sun!
- Hello, LJ.
It's hot. Not a cloud.
- Sleep well, LJ?
- Like at home.
- A little energy.
- Thanks.
At first, I didn't have fun
with my teammates.
Now, with the new Solana,
I have fun with everyone.
I open it and you catch it.
Seventeenth day,
and I'm having fun like never before.
He is thick.
And feel how heavy it is!
But it's a bit boring,
to be honest.
Mail!
'Cause there's
no fuss, no shenanigans,
no spying...
I like that, you know?
Let's see what it is.
“Pack the necessities
for the next 22 days.
And go to the Aparri camp,
where you will stay until the end of the game."
Good.
We have to stay strong.
Don't forget what we went through here.
It was too good to be true.
Merging is both
exciting and scary.
It's six against five.
We could be in trouble.
Thank god I still have
that immunity idol.
This idol is like
one more person in my alliance.
We are five, plus the idol.
If anyone from Solana
needs it, I'll play it.
So I believe we are
in a good situation.
"Maybe we should tidy up
a bit and make some space."
"Guests from Solana
will be arriving soon."
"And some may well
stay for the next 22 days."
We did it!
The tribes come together.
I believe it's a merger.
I hope.
In any case, the others arrive,
we will live on the same beach.
They come here?
It says they could stay
for the next 22 days.
But it will be three days for one,
six days for another...
We have reached the majority merger.
When these five arrive,
it will be them against us.
I won't let anyone forget it.
I believe there is
something going on.
- Is it a rowboat?
- Yes.
They better have food.
We come in peace!
Do you bring food?
We bring back everything we took from you!
We will make the chain.
When they arrived, I was nervous
to see my former teammates again.
It was like an old friend
you haven't spoken to in years.
It's good to be home!
The mosquito net is back.
Don't let go, the wine is in it!
They started unloading
their belongings and food.
Do you see the bread?
And I did...
We have a nice picnic.
Spencer, nice
to finally meet you!
- I am Jefra.
- Nice to meet you.
I am Sarah.
I see you've lost...
a teammate.
I didn't expect
my girlfriend Alexis to leave.
We were very close,
I could have easily poached her.
"Dung!
What to do now?".
Let's read that.
"Congratulations,
your tribes are merged."
We have achieved fusion!
"Enjoy the feast,
you've earned it."
"Hidden idols
are always in play."
"And an idol with special powers
is hidden near your camp."
- I'm shivering.
- "Special powers"!
Has this ever happened?
A special-powered immunity idol
?!
They are powerful enough already,
but with special powers?!
A different power.
This sends you home.
I do not want it!
There is only one way
to know these special powers,
is to find that idol.
Of course, I will look for her.
For two, three, four days.
It's weird to be back.
You have to think of a tribal name.
Solarri?
- Mix Solana and Aparri?
- Yes.
- So... - How
about we talk about it while eating?
There is wine...
Oh my God! Look at this!
Look!
Dude, it's Christmas!
Part of the excitement of the merger was
the shock of getting there.
I was in last place,
in one of the worst tribes
in Survivor history.
And here I am at the fusion,
with a new life.
I have control.
I'm close
to Sarah and Jeremiah,
close to that group of six
who could rule the game.
- So you took Alexis out.
- Eh yes.
Yeah, give us the scoop!
She attacked me,
I eliminated her.
We could be in trouble.
Six against five is tough.
My only hope is Sarah,
who is an ex-Aparri.
She swore on her badge
to stay with me.
My fear is that
if Sarah does not change sides,
we're screwed, I'm screwed.
I don't want to be screwed.
We've reached fusion,
do you believe it?
Inhale deeply.
Never release your abs.
Maintain tension.
And keep your shoulders straight. So.
It's good.
You're pretty flexible, Tash.
- Yes.
- It's certain.
Release.
Once again.
Inhale...
I'm going spearfishing
and resting a bit.
Who is the head of the snake,
in your opinion?
I do not know.
Intelligence seems to form a core.
At this point there is a group
of five, my alliance,
and a group of six,
half Intelligence, half Beauty.
And then there is Sarah,
the sixth person.
I want to talk to Sarah,
we had a real bond before.
You have to patch things up with her.
I will try
to bring her back to us.
We need someone who rocks.
We'll turn things around,
and it'll be us six against them five.
I hope Sarah
is our missing link.
How do you position yourself
now?
Honestly, I hesitate.
What happened...
- Then no need to think.
- The Intelligents are welded.
If we get back together, listen:
Sarah, Tony, Woo and Trish.
- Do we have Trish?
- She's with me 100%.
That's five. It makes equality.
LJ and Jeffra.
We are six and they are five.
They will leave one by one,
it's as simple as that.
I want Sarah to believe
that I want her with me in the final,
as we said,
two cops in front of the jury.
I'm going to promise her, guarantee it,
whatever it takes to reassure her,
that she believes that I am sincere,
that I want her with me
to advance in the game,
unlike the other tribe.
It can be very simple.
If you give me your word...
Swear on your badge.
- Swear on my badge?
- That you are with us.
Whether you'll vote
for Spencer or Lindsey.
No, Spencer or Kass.
- Spencer or Kass?
- Yeah.
I don't know if I can, Tony.
Let's advise later.
Tell me when you're ready.
And if you swear on your badge,
that's fine with me.
I have the best
possible position in this game.
Five against five, and I'm in the middle.
A sarah sandwich.
It's perfect!
- So who to target?
- Doesn't matter.
But I think we have to
separate the Intelligents.
So, anyone but me!
I guarantee you that with us,
you will advance.
It's guaranteed.
It's your turn.
This is your chance.
I didn't expect
to be able to decide.
It is a difficult situation.
But whatever my choice,
I am in a good position.
Because I will decide
the future of this game.
Alright, friends.
You want to know everything?
I want to know what you know.
LJ doesn't have an idol,
so if he doesn't win immunity,
he's leaving, because we would vote
for him, wouldn't we?
I think he has an idol.
I don't think he should
go first.
- Someone has an idol.
- And it's not me.
- LJ has an idol?
- Yeah.
I don't have an idol,
so I think LJ does.
This is what worries
me and makes me nervous.
I think
Jefra should go first.
No. It's LJ or Woo.
You have to take out a tough guy.
We need to get rid
of Woo or LJ.
It can't be LJ, because...
I'm afraid he has the idol.
So it must be Woo.
But if it's not Woo,
it will be Trish.
No. Very bad idea.
She is not dangerous.
It's silly to argue with me.
I'm not saying that
I should be treated like a princess,
but it would be better
not to cross me.
We can pretend,
but it don't have to be LJ,
for I fear he has an idol.
Yeah, that would be a bad idea.
But I
disagree with Trish.
It would be fatal for us.
What if Woo wins immunity?
It won't be LJ.
- Tony, then?
- Yeah.
I can do whatever I want.
Are you looking for a fight with me?
I will go with the camp opposite.
Don't provoke me,
because I will make you leave.
Trish and Jefra can stay.
You have to eliminate a guy.
- You don't think "long term".
- You know what?
Trish is close to Tony.
She's not from LJ.
I don't trust the cop.
When a member of a supposed
alliance of six says:
"I will only vote for such and such,
and in no case for such and such.",
That tells me
she's not in the six.
She is in one.
If there are six of us,
we can't make a fuss.
I don't want
anyone to force my hand, like...
Nobody is forcing you.
We talked about it before on the beach.
I never accepted
that Trish was the first.
Everything will be alright.
We'll talk again tomorrow.
We will meet
and the majority will decide.
Right off the bat, Tony tells me:
"If you come with us,
you choose who goes."
"If I go
with my old teammates,
they'll let me choose who goes.",
"That's who I want out.".
- We will speak about it tomorrow.
- But I don't force my hand.
Nobody accuses you of it.
Nobody should have that
much power in this game.
Who made her queen?
I can't look at her anymore.
I want to hit her sometimes.
Do you see fish?
- Is that a sea cucumber?
- A blue starfish.
I'm going to sit on this log.
I'm tired of people only
talking to me to get my vote.
"What are you going to do?
What are you going to do?"
It will get awkward,
after the first tip.
Because they won't talk to you anymore.
I won't talk to you anymore then.
You don't get
what I'm saying.
I like when people
lose their temper.
- That's telling.
- What did I miss?
This morning, things were heating
up between the two girls.
I believe
it's between Kass and Sarah.
The dispute made me happy,
because I realized that these six
are not so close together.
And it cracks before
we even go to the test.
Obviously, they're
all feeling a little paranoia.
What happened?
We didn't agree
on who to eliminate.
You said
you wouldn't vote for Trish.
Yes, because I find the idea
very bad.
I spent eleven days with her.
She doesn't strategize.
I see both points of view.
I don't want us to be divided
over nonsense.
When I found out about the trade
between Kass and Sarah,
I didn't care
who was right or wrong.
My only concern
was to reconcile them.
Your situation is difficult.
You are in a precarious situation,
I respect that.
It's your old friends,
and now you have new ones.
And everyone is
trying to attract you.
Who should we vote for?
If we don't vote LJ,
then Tony or Woo.
Tasha took
Sarah's side in our argument.
And then damn!
Someone treats
someone else in the alliance badly,
and everyone gives in to the tyrant?
"And me?
Why not be cool with me?"
I count for butter?
Ah, I don't interest you anymore!
When people say "I will not vote
for such and such", it makes me nervous.
And I am accused of being tyrannical,
I am not a tyrant! I'm trying...
Go on...
It doesn't matter that Kass likes me.
As soon as I say something,
here's the reaction, it's like...
It's like... If you attacked me
silently, like...
I attack you when I do "what"?
It's an attack, right?
Tell me, is it important
that Kass likes you?
If you don't like Kass,
vote against her!
I know Sarah and Tasha
are against me.
I know my situation.
At this point, all six break down.
- You realize that your role is central.
- And it sucks.
It will determine the fate of five
other people. In this game.
- No, it will determine your fate.
- Yours.
Yeah.
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all, I'm taking up
tribal immunity.
There is no more tribal immunity.
This is what you want now.
Individual immunity.
With this around your neck,
you are protected on the board.
No better feeling
in the world than wearing this.
Without, you could
be in trouble.
Today
you will balance
on triangular platforms,
in the water,
feet on very narrow
points of support.
Periodically, you step up
a notch, increasing the difficulty.
If you fall, you are eliminated.
The last person standing wins
immunity and is protected from voting.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be eliminated.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
OK, let's go!
Everyone get in place!
Place your feet
on the first support point.
Let's go.
Everyone is on their feet,
and the ordeal begins.
The rules are simple.
Only your feet can
touch the structure.
But not your hands, or your buttocks.
If that happens, you're out.
You will stay there for 15 minutes.
Think of it as a warm-up.
Relax.
Prepare your body for what is to come.
We go to the next support point.
You can help yourself
with your hands.
Everyone settle in well.
Let's go.
5... 4... 3... 2... 1...
Everyone take their hands off.
This ordeal begins again.
You're going to have
to hold on a little harder.
There is less space for your feet.
Everyone seems to be doing well.
Where do you hurt, LJ?
Everywhere.
This ordeal is clearly
no fun, Jeff.
It is very painful.
We have another
15 minutes.
Thirty seconds left
in this round.
Then we will go to the top.
Everyone is holding up well,
I'm impressed.
What you are doing is working.
What you tell yourself to hold on to,
keep repeating it to yourself.
Fifteen seconds. Don't
relax, don't give up.
You've held out so far,
don't make a mistake now.
We go to the top.
You can use your hands.
But if you fall now,
you're out.
You have fifteen seconds
to settle down.
Spencer falls, he fails
to make the transition!
Kass fails
to transition!
LJ has fallen!
Sarah has fallen!
Jefra has fallen!
They are only six!
Tasha is eliminated!
Trish is eliminated!
Four people survived!
Jeremiah has fallen!
More than three!
The wind knocks Morgan down!
The wind is unleashed!
It's between Tony and Woo!
Nice recovery from Tony!
They are only two!
Tony and Woo!
Great balancing act.
This last round got
the better of everyone except those two!
How are you feeling, Woo?
Stay focused!
Don't get distracted!
New beautiful recovery from Tony.
Someone is going to deserve that
first individual immunity.
- Good luck, Woo!
- Tony falls!
Woo wins the first
individual immunity!
Good game.
Woo, come here!
Just here.
The first individual immunity.
Woo is protected at tonight's council.
As for you, after 19 days,
someone will be eliminated.
The afternoon
should be interesting.
Pack your things, get back
to camp, we'll see you at the council.
Congratulation.
The first immunity, my brother.
- Nice job, Woo.
- It was hard.
You delivered, Tony.
No idea, man.
Wow, well done.
There are eleven people.
A core five,
a core five, and me.
I have to decide.
It makes sense that
the martial arts teacher won.
There are
more serious competitors on Tony's side.
I was the first in the water.
I would rather go with
the weak, the new Aparri.
The alliance is solid.
There's just the dissension
between Kass and me.
Shall we fetch water
now or later?
Let's go now.
I'll decide
who leaves next.
It's me who decides.
I'm the President, for now.
Who do you want?
Jeff, I think.
I think
the smartest one is Jefra.
Exactly what I thought.
There is no chance
that an idol will be played,
no chance of her having one.
I don't think any of them have an idol.
We need to get rid
of someone vital in the game.
Jefra will not win immunity,
we can eliminate him whenever we want.
And she's not smart enough
to play strategically.
Tony is very smart and observant.
I will vote for LJ or Tony.
Look at them!
Tony, don't trust Sarah.
We think she's in control.
Yes, because they
put her on a pedestal.
They need his vote.
Like us. So I will do the same.
Sarah will never leave them.
She is comfortable there.
She leads the dance.
She is the center of the group.
She is the most powerful
player of the moment.
They need his vote.
Do you really think you
can convince her to...
- Just yesterday...
- But not today.
Did you see that pussy fight?
It was today, and I do
n't think Kass is comfortable.
I can approach Kass,
I have a good contact with her.
Let me
talk to Sarah first.
If that's okay with you, I'll do it.
What if you think she's lying?
Am I going to see Kass?
Kass will play you.
So, what are we doing tonight?
I want Tony out.
Alright, but I'm afraid
he has an idol.
I guarantee you he doesn't.
If you think there isn't...
Let's vote Tony, then.
OK. As long as
everyone agrees.
Originally, we were supposed to stay cool
and eliminate Jefra or Trish,
to be in the majority.
And only then
take care of the big boys,
who might have
idols and strategies.
I hope that all will be well.
But Sarah wanted
it to be Tony.
She thinks she's the boss.
Is there anything to say
to possibly save me?
Yes, find an idol.
Am I the only one seeing it?
I know she will destroy the game.
And in this case, I want to strike
preemptively. I want to destroy it.
If you come with us, there are five of us...
It's exactly the same opposite.
But without Trish, Woo and me,
who you started with.
For Trish and me, you pass
LJ, Jefra and Woo.
So you're third,
along with Trish and me.
I want to think about it alone.
If you go with them,
let's say you eliminate me,
or LJ, whatever, one of us.
We are only four.
And you are six. Six against four.
They can eliminate you,
and there are still five of them.
They don't need you.
You don't have anyone there.
Nobody, Sara.
It's stupid. I know all that.
I'm not stupid.
Eliminating Tony
is not personal.
It's actually paying him
a big compliment.
Tony and I have a relationship
because we're both cops.
But it is the most dangerous.
He observes everything.
He is sneaky.
He is exactly like me.
And I would eliminate myself if I could.
If you want Kass gone,
we swear on our badges,
you want her to go,
come with us and she's gone.
If you're ready,
we'll do it for you.
- You're turning the game upside down now.
- I say.
I don't want
you to think I'm tricking you.
Let me digest that.
I do not say no.
But I won't make up my mind
until I'm on the council.
Tony, it's going to play.
No need to worry.
No. Everything is fine.
When Sarah tells me
she wants to think,
that she will decide at the council...
Serious? I can't
believe she said that!
I think now
that she will not join us.
One thing is certain,
at the slightest doubt, I play the idol.
I will not go with the idol.
You're at the bottom of your alliance,
I thought you were at the top.
I have been replaced.
If one of us leaves,
then they will eliminate you.
Interested in joining us?
I don't think
that's doable.
If you could eliminate anyone
on your team, who would it be?
I would eliminate Sarah.
Yes, that would sound good to me too.
It was more or less our idea.
I propose. Up to you to decide.
Trish tried to put me to sleep.
She told me
they were going to vote for Sarah.
It suprised me.
But maybe they're
smarter than I thought.
Probably more
than my other five.
If they think
Sarah is the problem,
maybe I'll change sides.
Let's go. We're eliminating it tonight.
Why?
I spoke with Kass.
- I asked him...
- These two don't get along.
Listen. I asked
her who she would like to eliminate.
She said Sarah.
I begged her to join us.
She thought it was impossible,
but I told her no.
- So you want...?
- Sarah.
We're voting for Sarah tonight.
Vote with us
and we'll take care of you.
Trust me.
I love that Sarah
thinks she's the boss.
The new Aparri votes for Tony,
at the request of Queen Sarah.
Solana votes for Sarah.
I really believe I am in the middle.
I believe I usurped
Sarah's throne tonight.
Once again, "Chaos-Kass"
will show up on the council.
So, LJ, where are we?
What is the mood
of this group of eleven?
I do not know. I believe I have
the most difficult position.
And if I leave, I'll be flattered,
it's the worst-best compliment
you can receive,
to be the most dangerous in the game.
Tasha, well said.
He is ready to leave,
to extinguish his torch.
At this stage of the game,
we are looking for the most dangerous,
so he has a lot to worry about.
Tony, the old Aparri
stayed together, except for Sarah.
Now there is the new Aparri
and the new Solana.
Do you notice different groups
coming together?
Indeed, Jeff.
But these people are smart,
and I hope they realize
that it is not
with the majority that we advance,
but with a pleasant alliance,
with whom one feels good.
Sounds like you're
worried about your fate.
It's true, Jeff,
I'm a little worried.
I come from a minority tribe in number.
And I could be a threat.
I'm 40,
I'm bald and old,
but the flame
still burns within me.
Are Kass, Tony and LJ
right to be concerned,
considering there is
a group of six and a group of five?
Yes, I would worry
if I was a strong male,
who assures in hardships,
in the minority group.
LJ, when do idols
come in?
Do you think we found them,
does anyone have one?
Since no idol appeared,
it could be
a good Survivor joke.
I do not know.
- There wouldn't be?
- There are idols. I have one.
And I will use it for my tribe.
- Do you have an idol?
- Sure.
- Do you want to take her out?
- What will that prove?
- That you are telling the truth.
- And what does it get me?
- You tell us you have one, so...
- All right.
There she is.
Inquiring minds want to know.
Inquiring minds want to see.
There she is.
I will wear it with pride.
And that doesn't mean
I'll use it for myself.
I can give it to LJ, to Jefra, to Trish.
He's a community idol.
So you're planning
on making a big splash tonight.
It'll be a big hit, Jeff.
Look at these six.
Look what's going on, Jeff.
Look at them!
- The other?
- And Spencer and Tasha change their vote.
They can change everything.
The other.
- It's debatable.
- A moment.
The other. Yes, the other.
Look at this!
We stay the same. The same. The same.
Do we put an end
to the suspense and move on to the vote?
Absolutely.
We are impatient.
Well, we vote for the other.
It's cool!
I love it when it's so alive.
It's time to vote.
Trish, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Can you confirm
that it is valid?
Can you confirm that for me, Jeff?
Yes, it is an immunity idol.
I would like to give it to LJ.
Let's see if I
read these people right, Jeff.
Votes against LJ
will not count.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
- Hold on, Jeff.
- Yes?
I would like to protect
Tony's back.
Yo, I bring!
I hate you.
You should not have.
But I appreciate.
Because I think you are "the other".
He is also
an immunity idol.
Votes against Tony
won't count either.
Unbelievable.
I thought you were "the other".
Let's see what happens.
I will read the votes.
Let it be Tony!
First vote...
Jefra.
Sarah.
Two Jefra votes,
two Sarah votes.
Jefra.
Sarah.
New equality.
Three Youfra votes,
three Sarah votes.
Jefra.
Sarah.
New equality.
Four Youfra votes,
four Sarah votes.
Jefra.
Sarah.
Equality.
Five Youfra votes, five Sarah votes.
One vote remains.
Seventh person eliminated
and first member of the jury...
I'm tremble.
Who betrayed?
Not me.
Sarah, the tribe has spoken.
- It's time to go.
- Thanks.
- Good luck!
- Thank you, Sarah.
Kass...
Well done, Kass.
We lost two idols,
but we will get them back.
Zero chance of winning the game.
The road is long.
This vote was clearly a shock.
I predict the sequel
will be tumultuous.
Take your torches, return
to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
I will speak harshly
to you because you speak harshly to me.
It's a war of words
between two Survivors.
She's a sour old woman.
But it's nothing
compared to the chaos
created by a hidden idol.
It's a crazy treasure hunt.
I go into ninja mode.
I was completely calm,
waiting for Jeff to
come up with the last name,
and when I saw "Sarah",
I went "huh?".
We thought we had
a solid group of six.
I don't know why Kass
changed sides,
but they got me.