translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Ninth person eliminated and
- LJ.
Taking LJ by surprise,
Tony did the same with his allies.
Now Trish, Kass and I
feel like we're last.
You don't want to be the prankster
? You are free!
And no one felt
more betrayed than Jefra.
Maybe it's time
I played my own game.
Having betrayed his alliance,
Tony needed a backup plan.
My God!
He found one, in the form
of an idol with different powers.
Can we play
it after seeing the votes?!
Everyone will do...
But Jefra had his own plan.
They made a big hit
without telling me.
Eliminate Tony
with the Minority Alliance.
- Final square?
- Final square.
On the camp...
Tony, we need to be able
to trust you.
Tony tried to regain
the trust of his allies.
I swear on my baby,
I swear on my father,
I swear it on my mother,
I swear it on everyone.
And at the tribal council...
You can steal all the clues
you want from me, Woo. I have it for real.
Spencer played his idol.
Jeffra backtracked.
And the alliance of five remained united.
Jeremiah, bring me your torch.
Leaving
Spencer and Tasha on the sidelines once again.
Jeremiah, the tribe has spoken.
- Goodbye everyone.
- Hi.
There are seven left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
I'm tired tonight.
Before the advice, I thought that
it was a good idea
to join Jeremiah, Tasha and Spencer.
Because I wanted
to turn against Tony.
But I'm in this alliance,
and I'm trying to take a step back.
I thought it would be worse for me
to face Tasha and Spencer at the end.
Where did this idol come from?
- Is it the river one?
- Yes.
I found her the day
Woo stole the clue from me.
I knew you had it,
by your behavior.
You're generally
meaner to me.
OK.
I felt
like Spencer had the idol.
As a good 21-year-old male,
he was not going to give it away.
What is the most selfish animal
on this planet?
A college-aged male.
Kass more or less
made the decision.
Not "more or less". She said
right off the bat, "Spencer has the idol."
Yes, I spent time with him.
And was going to vote for you,
and we thought...
He's too calm,
he's not like usual.
I've seen you often
when you think you're eliminated.
It impresses me,
if it's really true.
I used the idol,
and I used it wrong.
I lost my idol,
I lost my main ally,
and Tasha and I are
a two person army,
against this army of five,
of the "Goliath" type.
But the thing is,
Tasha and I are still here.
We lost the battle tonight,
but not the war.
It was great.
We made the idol go away.
Yes, it was perfect.
I like when a plan comes to fruition.
That's what I thought.
Mail!
I hope it says "congratulations,
celebrate with a feast".
Trish, look under my t-shirt.
Returning from the mail,
Woo says "my back hurts".
"Damn, are you okay?",
and I lifted.
I almost got knocked out
seeing the wallets.
I knew it was the auction,
I was really excited.
Because at least I was going to
be able to eat something.
That's all I wanted, to
eat something other than rice.
"You've seen it before.
Now you are.
If you really want something,
you better be quick."
To eat!
Historically, each time
there are auctions,
there is always some advantage
for a test.
The instant Jeff opens
- "500!".
I want this advantage.
And I don't want
Spencer or Tash to have it.
- Auctions!
- Great.
- At auction!
At this point,
either Tasha or I leave.
So we have to
be aggressive in these auctions.
Our life depends on it.
Over here, everyone!
Welcome to Survivor Auctions.
Each of you has $500.
Bids are $20 minimum.
You cannot
share money.
share food.
Bidding will stop without warning,
so if you like something,
bid.
- We begin?
- Yes.
First article. I discover it.
Popcorn, candy and soda.
- $40.
- $40 for Kass.
- 60.
- 60 for Youfra.
Once, twice...
Sold to Trish for $80.
Sweets and...
So taste a sample
right away.
Gum!
Damn it.
It's too good.
- Enjoy!
- Thanks.
- Good game.
- Yeah, good deal.
Sorry, buddy.
I know you love this.
Good. Next article.
It will stay covered.
The following article will remain covered.
80 for Tasha.
- 100.
- 100 for Youfra.
Once, twice...
Sold to Jefra for $100. Come!
So come!
$100, please.
There you go, sir.
That $100 gets you...
Probably pig's brains.
Quesadillas and guacamole!
That's what I wanted!
I've been talking about it all morning,
haven't I?
From quesadillas, from guacamole,
from salsa, et...
What's better with that
than a Margarita?
Glad to have done business
with you, sir.
Damn, that looks good!
Sorry.
Take a big bite of guac'!
Next article.
It will remain covered.
- $20.
- 20 for Kass.
No one is bidding
on Kass' $20.
Sold to Kass for $20.
You are bound to win.
Tony, damn it,
start bidding!
You are starving!
Before I show you
what you have...
You just bought this.
Let's go.
Here it gets interesting.
If you want,
you can trade with that.
I take the big one.
I prefer blue to red,
so I take blue.
I won't show you
what you've given up,
but here is what
you bought for $20.
Hold off.
Steak sandwich and iced tea.
- Taste it!
- Damn it, Jeff!
Damn it.
I would have devoured it on the spot.
My stomach is in knots.
I didn't know if I was going
to resist the temptation.
It's too good.
Take it!
- Look at this!
- Unbelievable.
I was shaking, my head was spinning,
but I had to restrain myself.
I was not going to leave
without an advantage.
I wish I could share.
Can I share?
No, and that's so good.
That way you can say
that you would like to do it.
Kass did not want this article.
Let's put it up for auction.
- 40.
- 40 for Woo.
Woo finally launches. You
missed a lot of food.
I give up.
What are you waiting for?
Once, twice...
Sold to Trish for $60.
give you this.
Disgusting!
- What's this?
- Rice!
I can still bid,
I have some money left.
What are you waiting for?
Bid, rapiats!
Do you want to eat or what?
Next article.
I show it to you. It's quite pretty.
Big pork chops
and a cold beer.
- 40.
- 40 for Woo.
Tony still doesn't move.
No Spencer Bid.
Tasha shows no interest.
I am amazed.
$40, once, twice...
Awarded to Woo.
Possibly the best deal
at all of Survivor's auctions.
Well done, Woo.
Since so few people
were fighting over food,
demand determined the market.
Terrific business.
All this food
for so little money.
I couldn't even look.
What do you expect?
What taste?
The spiciness of barbecue sauce.
The tenderness of the meat.
Let it explode in my mouth.
Go for it!
- Tender.
- Juicy.
- Covered with barbecue sauce.
- Wonderful.
Take it easy, Woo.
This is how we do it!
Enjoy!
- He's going to end up woo-re.
- Well done, Woo!
Damn, it looked
smaller there.
Clearly something is going on.
I show you splendid articles.
You haven't eaten for a month.
What's going on, Tony?
What do you want?
I hope for an advantage.
Probably my only chance to beat
these big guys in trials.
Spencer, what are you waiting for?
The same as Tony.
-Tasha?
- Could also be an advantage.
So three people
are hoping for a benefit.
So let's go?
Good. Next article.
At your request,
this is an advantage in the game.
- 500!
- A moment.
Here are the rules for these auctions.
If the bids reach
the maximum of $500,
then anyone who wants to
bet $500 can.
But beware.
If more than one person is $500,
you are not bidding
on advantage,
but on a chance to draw
lots for the gain of the advantage.
That's what you wanted.
Go ahead or shut up.
Are you giving up?
You waited for an advantage,
and now you give up?
Yes, Jeff.
Spencer and Tony, come here.
Good luck, sir.
- My friend.
500 from Tony.
And everything Spencer has.
You didn't intend
to bid on food.
There are two stones here.
One is black.
The other is white.
Black wins.
OK?
Don't look at it, hide it.
Do not look.
Palms up.
Three, two, one.
Black is the advantage.
Tony fired black.
You get this for $500.
An advantage in the game.
For $500, you get
a white pebble, you can keep it.
Well done, Tony.
This concludes Survivor's bidding.
Damn it!
I was hoping that Jeff
would submit one more article,
and that it would be
a clue about an idol.
But alas, I left
empty-handed.
And so, to stay,
I have to win immunity.
Damn it!
I was going to vomit, just watching...
It was the best deal
I've seen at auction.
But do you see that?
It is an inextricable situation.
We are starving, we have no energy.
So even if it is an advantage,
someone like Woo, who ate
those ribs, surely will... See?
You, who have lost,
are hungry and without advantage.
- I'm the one fucked.
- It's rough.
It's like that.
We knew what to expect.
I know, it's rough.
I needed
an advantage in the game.
Because my head
is the first on the block.
I was devastated.
I pull the pebble, I open my
hand, and the pebble is white.
Just a white pebble.
I have a new title.
I'm the biggest loser
in Survivor auction history.
Here's my rock,
I'm going to put it there.
I wanted to wait, but
everyone was waiting, and... $20!
I don't feel guilty
that Tony is the martyr of the band.
I've done enough.
I was happy.
I ate a huge dish.
And I could see Spencer
really frustrated, pull that head
that I know and love,
and that I wait at his house
when he knows he is in danger.
Take a nap.
My belly is going to explode.
All my allies have eaten.
I sacrificed myself,
I'm starving.
So I was a little disgusted.
Why take it all
on my shoulders?
Someone watch the fire and I'll
get some water? Or the contrary?
- So?
- I don't even eat bread.
Was it chicken quesadillas?
Chicken and cheese.
- Was there chicken?
- Yes, inside.
Sorry, ladies.
Someone watch the fire and I'll
get some water? Or the contrary?
- I'll get you some water.
- OK.
Not for me, for us.
The girls do nothing.
You wanted to eat,
I'm starving.
I sacrificed myself for this.
So while my allies
tell each other how good they feel
and discuss
what they ate,
I said I
was going for a walk.
May it be good.
"At the end of your beach, before
the rocks meet the sand,
you will find another idol,
hidden behind the bushes,
guarded by a tall white tree,
just a few centimeters
underground."
Good heaven!
I opened the tube
won at auction,
and this is not an advantage
in the next test,
but a clue
to find an idol.
"At the end of your beach...
Guarded by a large white tree."
It's a big white tree, isn't it?
Might as well start digging.
At this time,
I have an idol
with special powers,
and now, the possibility
of finding another idol,
that I could use
as I please.
Damn,
where is that big white tree?
If I find her,
I won't have to worry anymore.
When I have it, I will have the power.
Big how?
I love the ocean.
- Me too.
You don't have any at home?
No, and this is the first time
I've actually been there.
You're kidding.
I went on vacation,
but I was suspicious.
If the five stay together,
the people in danger
are Spencer and me.
So I want Tony to know
there's a possibility
let's form a female alliance
and eliminate it.
I want
Tony to see me talking to them.
To think that there are only ten days left!
Tony is unpredictable.
Just heat it up a bit,
and it will explode.
Tony, you are so skinny!
I say.
I'm not going back. Finished for me.
He is fading away.
It will restart it.
They've been in the water
for a while.
I see
Tash has his own plan.
She works girls,
can't you see?
She's great friends
with the girls now.
I've been telling you from the start,
she's a social player.
You're not worried that this girly thing will
work, are you?
I do not know. I do not think so.
You know, we weren't lying
when we said Jefra was with us.
She wanted to eliminate you,
it was not a canard.
When?
Two days ago.
She said they were trying
to figure out their best option,
and that they were planning
to eliminate you by surprise.
Jefra promised that 100%
she wanted to eliminate you.
Wow.
I'm trying to plant doubts
that will grow
and will cause
the division of this alliance.
It could involve
to create a false paranoia
around a female alliance.
Even if nothing like this happens,
it carries a lot
of weight right now.
She also told Tasha
that if it didn't get better,
she would be a big hit
at the next tip.
That's all I'm saying.
If I can make Tony paranoid,
that's gold.
Because Tony is crazy.
Tony is ready to play hard,
but not always well.
And it's great in this game.
Because if I can push the one
who dominates to make mistakes,
and to disconnect,
so I'm still here
and anyone could leave
at this point.
She is angry that she lost LJ.
She also said she was
sure she could get Trish back,
to vote against you.
And she changed her mind the next day.
I hate people like that.
When Spencer told me
the girls might be in cahoots
and want to eliminate the guys,
"oh there, gently".
"Don't believe Spencer right away,
he's desperate, but dig into the question."
I will keep that in mind.
I'm not going to talk about it,
spill the beans,
nor make hay around it.
"It's obvious".
"Guys
are dangerous, let's get rid of them."
And they can,
we are 4 girls and 3 guys.
If it's important,
I'll let you know.
Of course it's important, are
you kidding?
Do you think I'll wait
quietly to get out?
I promise you,
that's what she said.
All the clues show
that they want to eliminate me.
They don't want me to go all
the way. But I won't go.
I'll take matters
into my own hands, as usual.
He is really nice.
He's... It's Spence, I love him.
He will be a great guy.
He's so skinny,
he must be gaining weight.
I feel our alliance of five.
So I relaxed a bit.
It's good to know that there will be
no conflicts today.
Because whoever wins immunity,
we can fire Tash or Spence.
We see the light at the end of the tunnel.
Let's get this crab out,
it's probably already dead.
- He is dead?
- Yeah.
- Let's take it out. - Shit.
Hey, what do I do with the crab?
He is dead!
Is it okay if he died
in this heat?
- Put it in the water.
- There is no boiling water.
We collected kindling.
It needs to be cooked quickly.
- Otherwise, it will spoil.
- OK.
Shake your ass and cook it, then.
Did you hear?
It plays in the water
and it barks orders.
"You have to cook it quickly
or it will spoil."
So get moving and come bake it!
Put some water to boil!
I can not believe.
After all these discoveries
with Spencer,
"It's four girls
against three guys".
They may be up to
something, a big deal.
So I decided
to go find the idol.
It is the number one priority.
"At the end of your beach,
before the rocks."
"Guarded by a large white tree."
There's a big white tree.
That's a big white tree.
A big white tree.
"Hidden behind the bushes."
Let's always see.
And here it is!
I have been looking for her for so long.
Come see Dad!
I love you so.
That's what I was looking for.
This is the 3rd idol I find.
Right now, I have two idols
in my possession.
A special, and one
I can have fun with.
I can play it for myself, give
it to someone to create a surprise.
I am the king of the world,
the king of this game.
Owl. This is the secret idol?
No. That was the advantage.
Much better than an
in-game advantage, right?
- Lord.
- Was it worth fasting?
- Yeah.
- Look at this beauty.
- Cheer.
- She's for everyone.
You see? Like the other time.
I decided to show
this idol to my allies.
To each of them.
"I have the idol, we are protected".
It's better than an advantage
in the immunity test.
But what I'm really saying
is "I'm protected".
"Don't even think
about voting against me."
- She's a real one.
- Lord.
There are always four girls.
I tried
to scare them a little.
Just in case they consider
plotting against me.
They know I have an idol.
I've never been so happy
to have spent $500.
Over here, everyone!
- Ready for the immunity test?
- Yeah.
First of all, Tasha,
once again I get it back.
You might have
to fight for it, Jeff.
- Just win it back.
- Okay, good idea.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today
you will dig up bags.
When you have the five bags,
you will collect balls from them.
And you will move them
on a baffle table.
The first person to
bring their five balls to the end
gain immunity,
is protected from the vote,
and ensures a one in six chance
of winning this game.
The losers, tribal council,
where someone will be eliminated.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Let's go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
To dig,
and find the end of the rope
and the first bag.
When it's done, go ahead,
just shoot.
Tony has his, Tasha too.
Spencer has his.
Everyone goes
through this ordeal.
Jefra has hers.
Some bags will come quickly.
For others, you will have to dig.
Kass is still digging.
Trish is still digging.
Once at the end,
untie the bags and take out the balls.
Tony has all five.
Start untying them!
Woo has all five.
Tasha has all five.
Kass now shoots.
Trish is still looking,
she can't find the rope.
Spencer is still
on the 5th sack. Here he has it.
Trish has her rope,
she's in on it.
Spencer, Woo, Tony and Tasha untie
the bags and release the balls.
You have to take out all the balls
before going to the table.
Jefra has her fifth bag.
Start untying!
Tasha has all five balls,
she will be first to the table.
Tasha won
two individual immunities.
A third would be nice.
If the ball falls, start over.
Kass has his five bags.
It will start to detach.
Jefra has her five bags.
Trish has her five bags.
It may start to detach.
Everyone tries
to catch up with Tasha.
As usual,
Tasha places her first ball.
And soon his second.
Tasha places her second.
Two out of two!
Tony is at the table,
he has his five balls.
Spencer is now
at the table with her balls.
Woo has his five balls,
here he is at the table.
Tony freaks out
and scatters his balls.
It's subtle.
It takes touch and finesse.
Tasha is close to placing
her 3rd ball, but she falls.
It gives others a chance.
Woo places his first ball.
Tony places his first ball.
Tasha, leading with two.
Jefra joins the action,
she has her five balls.
Tasha places her third.
Tasha, leading with three.
More than two.
Woo places his second.
Spencer places her first.
Woo places his third.
Equality. Three for Woo,
three for Tasha
Spencer gets left behind.
Tasha all set to place her fourth.
Can she handle it
around the other balls,
towards this outer hole?
Tasha places her fourth.
He's only missing one.
Jefra, Trish and Kass lose their footing.
You need to get yourself back!
Four for Tasha, three for Woo.
Woo places his fourth.
He's only missing one.
Tasha is now close
to the goal with her fifth ball.
Can she get there?
Woo is all ready.
Who will win?
And she does!
Tasha gains immunity.
Protected at council tonight.
Thank you, Jesus.
Tasha, come here.
Once again,
immunity is yours.
Tasha, protected on the council,
she cannot be eliminated.
After thirty days,
someone will leave tonight.
Take your things, return
to camp. We'll see you at the council.
- Congratulation.
- Thanks.
Congratulations once again, Tash.
You are amazing. It was awesome.
Thank you.
Tasha is a beast.
For the third time in a row,
Tasha has immunity.
Having immunity
is essential at this stage of the game.
Everyday people
reconsider their covenants,
break their covenants.
The plan, by the way,
is to keep talking to the girls...
Shit, since Tony offers
the final trio to everyone,
perhaps he will suggest it to me.
...to make Tony wary of girls.
If he's freaking out for fear
they'll betray him, that's...
Either way, it's good for me.
And maybe also for Spencer.
Not good, mon ami.
Yeah, it wasn't...
- ...not the expected result.
- Yeah.
I wouldn't worry too much.
These trials were favorable to him.
Yeah. Both have to go, so...
Spencer tonight and Tasha next.
- Yeah.
- Where is everyone?
Spence and Tasha
went to get water.
It's good.
Maybe we should...
We were just talking about it.
- Yes, of course.
- What?
If Tash hadn't earned
that necklace, she was leaving tonight.
Of course, we know it's Spence.
Yeah.
So we have to pass
- Spencer.
- Can I join you?
- Sure.
It's the worst case scenario for me.
Tasha is still there,
there are still four girls.
Spencer gone,
only two guys left.
Not difficult to see
that it is four against two.
They can
eliminate us one by one.
So I have to go
after a girl from my alliance.
And the only one I can
blame is Jefra.
She was ready
to come after me.
to come after all of us.
Once again,
it's time to change the game.
What's up, Woo?
Want to roll someone tonight?
Doing what?
By eliminating Jefra.
And keep Spencer and Tasha?
Yes, precisely.
If we eliminate Spencer tonight,
you and I are finished.
- Yeah.
- Why?
The girl-boy ratio.
We have to eliminate a girl tonight.
So I'm gonna grab Spencer
- "Do you wanna stay?
Tasha wants you to stay?
Vote Jeffra.".
Tony is brilliant.
Nine times out of ten, we agree.
We looked at each other and knew
exactly what the plan would be.
We can't eliminate Spencer.
Do you agree with Jefra?
We have to think long term.
Absolutely.
Voting Spencer tonight
would be our end.
- OK.
- Here's the problem.
I won't be able to tell
Trish or Kass about my plan.
So we'll need
Spencer and Tash.
It's time for
me to play hero and save you.
I don't want
you to leave before Jefra.
I want to work with you
to eliminate Jefra.
But there is
only one way to achieve this.
I'm going to be hated because I won't tell
Trish or Kass about this.
- You tell me, Tash and Woo about it.
- Not Tash.
You'll be talking to Tash.
What I said to Tony
had an effect.
This paranoia about
a female alliance is perfect.
The key is convincing Tash.
It's your job.
Tash tells me she'll do
anything to help me stay.
She is my ally and my friend.
I know that she is
ready to act so that I stay.
Are you ready for "The Miracle
of Survivor Part 2"?
Good.
Spence, tell me
something positive.
Jefra.
Tony and Woo do
n't trust him or the girls.
They want to eliminate Jefra.
And they need us.
- What did you do?
- I tried to stay alive.
For two or three more days.
- Yeah.
- I will vote for Jefra.
Feeling hopeless, then receiving
a golden ticket for a 2nd chance,
it's incredible.
She's on.
OK, splendide.
Things seem to be improving,
but I don't
trust Tony that much.
If this plan fails, I'm out of the game.
So this new idol,
with maybe more powers,
could really help me.
Where is Spencer?
Don't tell me he's looking.
Woo, where's Spencer?
He is really looking for the idol!
It's frightening, alarming,
for him to do this while
I plot to save him.
So I wonder.
Eliminating Jefra, is it a good idea?
Is it good for my allies,
for my game?
Or would it be better to eliminate
a danger like Spencer?
Because Jefra is not dangerous.
And Spencer is awesome.
You saw what he did.
Do you need to talk, Tony?
Its good?
No one is speaking...
When the sun goes down,
it's time.
What to do at this point?
You could say
that I panic on my own.
But it's not me
doing that, it's the game.
Hey, Woo. It's going to be chaos
tonight, my friend.
Now here are
the members of the jury.
And Jeremiah,
eliminated at the last council.
Spencer, at
today's immunity challenge,
You and Tasha know you have to win.
- Correct.
- Tasha wins her third immunity.
And you come to the council
empty-handed.
Yes. You might think I'm in danger,
with this information.
I played my idol last time,
so I'm helpless.
Tony, what was the vibe
at camp after the event?
Jeff, it was chaotic.
Spencer tried to convince me
that one of my allies
was trying to take me as a traitor.
In this case, Jefra.
So you know what?
I don't want any nasty surprises.
I do not want to leave.
I was angry
about the elimination of LJ.
I would be lying
if I said otherwise.
So...
Jefra must have overcome her anger
at not having been warned.
We don't advertise
a surprise elimination.
We prevent it from being known
by those who could
screw it up.
Tony, are you surprised
that this group stays together,
considering the real dissensions
he knows?
We're left with just this, Jeff:
believe that we will continue
to move forward together.
If all goes well, two more votes
and we'll be the last five.
Spencer, if there's one thing
working in your favor,
That's right.
Chaos.
Chaos is great.
For now,
I'm clearly the target.
If I can shake the coconut tree,
chaos can only help me.
Kass, do you dread
that this family that seems to
be healthy and dysfunctional
becomes above all dysfunctional,
and Trish, or Jefra, or Woo,
or Tony makes a mistake?
A mistake could
be made tonight.
Tempers are heating up,
paranoia is everywhere.
Jefra, you nod.
That's it to the power of 10, Jeff.
Of course, when we are
on the start,
we try to sow discord
as much as possible,
hoping to divide us
and achieve something.
Spencer,
if you're really leaving tonight,
we can't accuse you
of not having made big moves.
What would be your conclusion?
I think I played well.
And I think I played hard.
I can leave
with this satisfaction.
But in this game,
opportunities arise.
Some may well
come true now.
If you eliminate me, then Tasha,
to finish 4th or 5th,
you will have made a mistake
by not acting tonight.
Most of the time
people lose at this game
because they did not act
when they could have,
because they were
too sure of their position.
I hope it won't happen
to anyone this time.
With that, it's time to vote.
Kass, it's up to you.
I saved you once,
I won't do it again.
The moral of the story:
"You have to play
before you are played."
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote...
Jefra.
Spencer.
Equality. Two Jefra votes,
two Spencer votes.
spencer.
Three Spencer votes, two Jefra votes.
Youfra, equality.
Three Spencer votes,
three Jefra votes.
One vote remains.
Eleventh person eliminated
and fifth member of the jury...
Jefra.
Good game.
Jefra, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck.
I had fun.
Once again,
your reactions are revealing.
Another surprise elimination.
If there was any doubt
about the individual character of this game,
it should be lifted tonight.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
Don't tell me what I said!
Everyone is tired
of Tony's antics.
- I could write your name.
- Do that and you'll be gone.
He's an idiot.
Even his closest ally.
- I am on it.
- Great.
At this point,
if I have to make a big move,
I will do it.
Clearly, someone
in the alliance betrayed me.
I suspect Woo and Tony,
because if Tony wanted to eliminate me,
Woo would follow.
They deceived me.
I should have changed sides
when I had the chance.
But I don't live in regret.
So that's how I played,
and that's how I come out.