>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": 18 NEW CASTEAWAYS
WERE DIVIDED INTO 32 TRIBES--
BRAWN, BRAINS, AND BEAUTY.
WELCOME TO KAY.
AT THE BEAUTY TRIBE, L.J. WAS
SUSPICIOUS OF MORGAN.
>> SHE EITHER ALREADY HAS AN
IMMUNITY IDOL OR SHE HAS A CLUE.
>> Jeff:
>> WE'RE STICKING TOGETHER.
HE'S GOT MY BACK.
>> AND THEY WENT TO WORK ON
RECRUITING JEREMIAH.
>> Jeff: MEANWHILE AT THE
BRAWN TRIBE, TONY HIT THE GROUND
RUN, FINDING AN IDOL--
>> THIS IS HUGE.
>> Jeff: AND MANIPULATING HIS
TRIBE.
>> ARE YOU A COP?
>> NO, WHY.
>> DO YOU SWEAR?
>> I SWEAR.
>> THOUGHT FOR A SPLIT SECOND
SHOULD I TELL THEM I'M A COP.
AND I SAID NO, THEY'LL TRY TO
BLINDSIDE ME RIGHT AWAY.
>> Jeff: THE BRAIN TRIBE
CONTINUED TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
BEAUTY WINS!
BLOWING A HUGE LEAD AND LOSING
THEIR SECOND CHALLENGE IN A ROW.
BACK AT CAMP, THINGS GOT WORSE.
GARRETT DECIDED TO HOLD AN OPEN
VOTE.
>> KASS, DO YOU HAVE ANY OPINION
ON THAT?
>> J'TIA.
>> Jeff: BUT IT BACKFIRED.
>> GATOR, YOU'RE AN IDNOT!
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THE WOMEN DECIDED STRATEGY WAS
MORE IMPORTANT THAN EATING.
THEY BLIZZARDED GARRETT, LEAVING
SPENCER THE ODD MAN OUT.
GARRETT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> WHO WANTS TO WELCOME ME TO
THE BOTTOM?
>> Jeff: 16 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> KUDOS, GUYS.
DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS A TRAIN
WRECK.
GARRETT WAS BAD ENOUGH AT THE
GAME THAT THE GIRLS WERE WILLING
TO CHOOSE SOMEONE WHO DESTROYED
ALL OF OUR FOOD OVERHIM, WHICH
IS CRAZY.
I'M DEFINITELY THE ODD MAP OUT
RIGHT NOW.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO RESORT TO
ALL KIND OF CRAZY, CREATIVE
IDEAS JUST TO HAVE A SHOT AT
THIS THING.
IF HE HADN'T DONE HIS WHOLE MOCK
TRIBAL COUNCIL--
>> HONESTLY, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
J'TIA TODAY IF HE HAD JUST HAD
THE PRIVATE CONVERSATION.
>> YEAH.
>> I CAME INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL
CLEARLY THINKING, YOU KNOW, IT
WAS ME GOING, BUT IT WAS A LOT
OF LUCK.
THIS TRIBE IS PRETTY MUCH A
COMPLETE DISASTER, BUT IT'S
ENTERTAINING SO WE'LL SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
I WAS VOTING J'TIA TODAY WHEN I
SAID I WAS NOT KIDDING.
>> WHEN DID IT CHANGE FOR YOU?
>> WHEN I FOUND OUT THAT YOU,
KASS, AND GARRETT HAD AN
ALLIANCE.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M STILL PISSED ABOUT THE
RICE.
I'M STILL PISSED AT J'TIA, BUT I
HAVE NO LOYALTIES TO SPENCER AND
I'M GOING TO TRY TO DO MY BEST
TO GET KASS ON BOARD FOR AN
ALL-GIRL ALLIANCE.
>> WELL, SPENCER IS GOING TO
SCRAMBLE.
>> HE'S THE NEXT TO GO.
>> I WAS THINKING ABOUT THAT,
TOO.
>> HE'S-- HE'S THE NEXT TO GO.
>> LET'S JUST GO IN AS GIRLS.
LET'S GO.
I HONESTLY DIDN'T KNOW WHO I'D
VOTE FOR WHEN I WENT INTO
TRIBAL, BUT THEN YOU THINK ABOUT
GATOR.
HE'S FUN TO LOOK AT, BUT YOU
DON'T WANT TO PLAY WITH HIM.
AND I THOUGHT J'TIA HAS
AATISMER, BUT YOU CAN REPLACE
RICE, AND NOW SHE'S SCARED, SO I
THINK SHE'LL BE LOYAL TO ME.
I HOPE YOU GUYS DON'T TURN ON ME
FOR SPENCER BECAUSE I JUST--
>> HELL NO.
>> IT WOULD BE--
>> I DON'T TRUST NOBODY HERE.
THEY'RE AGAINST ME, AND I'M BY
MYSELF, ME, MIERKZ MY IDOL AND
I.
NOW THERE'S FOUR OF US.
I WAS SITTING BY THE FIRE ALL BY
MY LOAN SHM AND SARAH CAME BY
AND I SAID LET ME GIVE HER
SOMETHING AND HE WHAT HAPPENS.
SOID SAY, "YOU KNOW WHAT, SARA,
LISTEN, I'M ALSO A POLICE
OFFICER.
YOU WERE RIGHT WHEN YOU TOLD
ME."
HOW DID I KNOW I WAS A COP.
>> I CAN JUST TELL.
I CAN JUST TELL.
I'VE BEEN A COP FOR SEVEN YEARS.
MY WIFE WAS A COP FOR EIGHT
YEARS.
>> I KNEW YOU WERE A COP.
I KNEW.
WE'RE GOOD.
YOU KNOW HOW PEOPLE SAY THEY
HAVE A GAY-DAR.
I HAVE A COP-DAR.
I CAN TELL WHO COPS ARE AND TONY
IS A COP.
I KNEW IT FROM DAY ONE AND HE
FINALLY TOLD ME.
I FELT LIKE I UP WITH THE
LOTTERY.
I WAS LIKE GOSH DANG IT, I KNEW
I WAS RIGHT.
NOW THEY KNOW TONY'S A COP,
WE'VE GOT THAT BLUE TBLOOD GOING
AND COP BLOOD RUNS THICK, SO HE
IS LOYAL TO COPS, AND YOU BETTER
BELIEVE I'M GOING TO STICK BY
HIS SIDE.
WE'RE GOING TO BE PARTNERS IN
CRIME.
>> I TOLD SARAH IN ONE
CONVERSATION THAT TOOK PLACE
BETWEEN CLIFF AND LINDY, BUT
THAT WAS A LIE.
THAT WAS A TOTAL LIE.
I JUST TOLD HER I HEARD STUFF,
JUST SO I COULD TRY TO GET HER
ON MY SIDE.
TO ME, IT MEANS NOTHING.
YOU COULD SWEAR ON YOUR KIDS,
YOUR FAMILY, YOUR DEAD
GRANDMOTHER-- IT DOESN'T MATTER
TO ME.
IT'S JUST WORDS.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH THIS RAIN,
MAN?
OH, COME ON.
THIS REALLY SUCKS.
>> MAN THIS IS-- THIS IS BRUTAL,
MAN.
>> THE WEATHER HAS BEEN THE MOST
MISERABLE EXPERIENCE I'VE EVER
ENCOUNTERED.
IT'S EITHER A MONSOON OR A
HURRICANE.
EVERYTHING IS SO WET.
I MEAN, ALL WE'VE GOT IS THIS
ONE LITTLE SPARK THAT I'M
DESPERATELY TRYING TO KEEP
ALIVE.
ALL THE WOOD IS WET.
WE'RE BASICALLY SCREWED.
>> IT'S MISERABLE.
ABSOLUTELY MISERABLE.
THIS IS TOUGH.
I'M MAKING A JOKE ABOUT THIS,
BUT THIS AIN'T FUNNY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
RIGHT?
THE SUN ALWAYS COMES OUT IN THE
MORNING.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> MAN, LOOK AT THAT WATER.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
>> SARAH!
IS THERE MORE?
>> THE RAIN IS NARLY,
TREACHEROUS, FREEZING, IT'S
POURING.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
BUT THIS IS WHAT "SURVIVOR" IS
ALL ABOUT, BABY.
HOPEFULLY IT WILL DIE DOWN HERE
SHORTLY.
IF NOT, IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG
NIGHT.
WHOOO!
>> GET SOME WATER TO DRINK RIGHT
HERE, KID.
OH, THAT'S GOOD, WOO.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN TRY FOR MORE
THAN A COUPLE OF HOURS ON THIS
ISLAND.
NONSTOP RAIN IS JUST REALLY BAD
FOR MORAL.
WE'RE ALL MISERABLE.
THIS IS WHAT I ENVISION HELL TO
BE LIKE.
>> I WISH WE WOULD HAVE WON THAT
TARP, MAN.
>> AH!
I MEAN, WE'VE BEEN UP THE WHOLE
NIGHT.
SINCE THE SUN WENT TOWN AT 6:30,
WE'VE BEEN SITTING HERE CUDDLED.
>> I GUESS I BROKE MY TOENAIL
OFF.
>> IT PROBABLY JUST CAME OFF
BECAUSE THEY'RE SOAKED.
>> THIS IS THE MOST RIDICULOUS
SITUATION I'VE EVER PUT MYSELF
IN.
AND I JUST WISH I HADN'T.
>> I'M SITTING THERE, AND I'M
LOOKING OVER AT LINDSEY, AND I
DO NOT FEEL BAD FOR HER, BECAUSE
I WAS TALKING WITH TONY LAST
NIGHT AT THE FIRE, AND HE GAVE
ME SOME TID BITS ABOUT CLIFF AND
LINDSEY HAVING A CONVERSATION
ABOUT ME.
SO IMMEDIATELY THAT JUST SET ME
OFF.
>> GIVE ME THE RUNDOWN.
>> ALL RIGHT, WHAT I HEARD WAS
THIS-- TRISH, WE CAN GET RID OF
HER AT ANY TIME.
WE CAN GET RID OF TRICIA REQUEST
TIME.
SARAH IS THE SMART ONE, THOUGH.
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID.
SARAH IS THE SMART ONE.
AND LINDSEY SAID, "SARAH?
OH, I LIKE SARAH.
I LIKE SARAH."
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> AND CLIFF IS THE ONE-- "HEY,
SHORTY, IT'S A GAME.
YOU GOTTA BE FOCUSED."
THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD HER.
I'M TELLING YOU.
>> I'M TELL YOU, THE BLUE BLOOD,
BABY.
>> WE FORMED COPS "R" US LAST
NIGHT I'M BEING SERIOUS, IF YOU
PANIC--
>> I'M NOT GOING TO.
THAT'S WHAT I CAME OUT, BECAUSE
I NEEDED TO FIND YOU.
>> IF YOU GO AGAINST YOUR WORD
AS "SURVIVOR" BUT DON'T SAY BLUE
BLOOD AND GO BEHIND MY BACK.
>> I WON'T.
THAT'S WHY I SAID THAT.
ABSOLUTELY.
HE KNOWS I'LL BE LOYAL TO HIM.
I KNOW HE'LL BE LOYAL TO ME.
WE SHOOK ON IT AGAIN TODAY.
IT'S THE MOST SINCERE HANDSHAKE
YOU'LL EVER HAVE IN YOUR LIFE.
I TRUST HIM 110%.
WHEN YOU FINALLY TOLD ME I WAS
LIKE, "YES.
I KNEW I WAS RIGHT."
ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NO MATTER WHAT YOU TELL
ANYBODY, YOU CAN'T TRUST THEM.
I DON'T TRUST NOBODY HERE,
NOBODY HERE.
NONE OF THEM.
AND I'M SURE THEY DON'T TRUST
ME.
>> I JUST WISH IS IT WOULD STOP
JUST FOR, LIKE, 10 MINUTES.
JUST LONG ENOUGH TO, LIKE, WALK
AROUND AND BREATHE A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT'S UP WITH ALL THESE FLIES?
I DON'T LIKE IT.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN IN A
"SURVIVOR" NIGHTMARE.
LAST NIGHT WE HAD A HORRIBLE
STORM.
OUR CLOTHES, THEY'RE COMPLETELY
DRENCHED.
IT'S HOPELESS TO GET THEM TRY
TODAY.
OUR FINGERS, AS YOU CAN SEE--
WE'VE BEEN IN SOAKING WET WATER
FOR ALMOST 24 HOURS NOW.
WE ALL STAYED UP ALL NIGHT LONG.
WE EVAPORATE HAD FOOD.
WE HAVEN'T HAD ANYTHING TODAY
BECAUSE WE CAN'T MAKE A FIRE.
REALITY HAS SET IN, AND IT'S
REALLY, REALLY, REALLY HARD.
I FEEL LIKE--
>> I THINK WE SHOULD THROW OUR
SUITS ON AND JUST GO IN THE
OCEAN?
>> I'M SCARED I'LL BE EVEN
COLDER.
>> WE NEED TO COME UP WITH
ANOTHER PLAN FOR TONIGHT BECAUSE
THIS ISN'T GOING TO WORK.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, JEFFER IS
DOING A LOT OF COMPLAINING
WITHOUT A LOT OF DOING, AND I
KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS-- JEREMIAH
AND L.J., GO ON, PREPARE THE
SHELTER.
IT TAKES A LOT OF HARD WORK TO
GET BY WHEN YOU'RE SURVIVING.
AND I GUESS THE STEREOTYPE OF
BEAUTY IS STARTING TO COME INTO
PLAY.
I MEAN, THESE GIRLS DON'T DO
ANYTHING.
I MEAN, THEY'RE ON SOME OTHER
SORT OF PLANET.
>> RIGHT NOW, IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
>> IT LOOKS DRIER.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY DRIER.
>> WE'RE DEFINITELY GOING TO
HAVE TO PUT PALM FROND OVER THEM
BECAUSE OTHERWISE THEY'LL BLOW
OFF.
>> I HAVE TO KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT.
THIS IS ONE OF THOSE SITUATION
WHERE'S I HAVE TO KEEP MY MOUTH
SHUT BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO PUT
ANY BULL'S EYES ON MYSELF.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN THROUGH A
MONSOON.
I GUESS I'M GETTING TO SEE IT
FIRSTHAND NOW.
>> I'M FREEZING.
( THUNDER ).
>> WE'RE WET, WE'RE SOAKED,
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET DRY ANY
TIME SOON, AND MY MIND IS ALWAYS
RUNNING SO I FIGURED ON THE
FIRST DAY WHEN I VOTE OFFSIDE
MORGAN AND WE SHOWED UP FROM
CAMP, SHE CAME AROUND THE REEF
AND ROCK.
THE FACT THAT SHE WAS THERE FOR
NO REASON.
YOU KNOW, SHE MUST HAVE GOT A
CLUE.
SO I FIGUREUD THAT, YOU KNOW,
WHAT?
MAYBE I'LL JUST TAKE A PEEK.
MAYBE I'LL SEE IF I CAN FIND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
WHO THE HELL LOOKS FOR A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL IN THE MIDDLE OF A
TOO FOON BUT THIS GUY.
AND THAT'S WHY I FOUND OUT.
I HAVE THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I'VE GROWN OFF ON "HARD WORK
PAYS OFF."
YOU REAP WHAT YOU SOW.
NOW I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
TO HIDE IT.
I'M KEEPING THIS A SECRET.
NO ONE IS EVER GOING TO KNOW I
HAVE THIS THING UNTIL I PLAY
THIS THING.
>> OUR FAVORITE PLACE.
>> WE HAVE TREE MAIL.
IT'S GOT A LITTLE--
>> TELL US SOMETHING GOOD,
PLEASE.
>> WE'VE GOT A LITTLE GUY ON
HERE.
>> A LITTLE--
>> LIKE A BUDDHA.
IT MIGHT BE A MEDITATION
CHALLENGE.
WHOEVER CAN MEDITATE FOR THE
LONGEST.
>> WHO WANTS TO READ?
I DO.
"MULE BE MAZED AND CONFUSED.
THIS MUCH IS TRUE."
>> A MAZE.
>> "IN THIS CHALLENGE, THE TRIBE
WORKS TOGETHER, TOSSING SMALL
BUCKETS OF WATER FROM THE OCEAN
INTO A LARGER BUCKET ON THE END
OF A TEETER-TOTTER.
WINNING IMMUNITY MEANS A DRIER
SHELTER, TOO."
>> A TARP.
>>
>> I'M EXCITED TO EAT RICE.
>> YEAH, WE GOTTA GET SOME RICE
GOING.
>> WE GOTTA IT'S SOMETHING.
>> AND WATER.
>> J'TIA DUMPED OUT 95% OF OUR
RICE, BUT SHE'S ASKING HOW MUCH
RICE SHOULD WE COOK?
AND I'M LIKE, "ARE YOU FREAKING
KIDDING ME RIGHT NOW?"
IT'S I WERIC.
IT'S A MESS AROUND HERE.
WE HAVE AN IMPENDING CHALLENGE.
SOMEONE COULD POSSIBLY GO HOME
AND MY FIRST INCLINATION IS
LET'S PRACTICE.
CAN WE DO EVERYTHING AS QUICKLY
AS POSSIBLE BECAUSE I WANT TO
PRACTICE DIFFERENT TECHNIQUES.
>> I'M GOING TO DO A LITTLE
INTERIOR DECORATING.
>> I'M SORRY, BUT I'M A LITTLE
DEHYDRATED.
I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE LOOKING AT
ME LIKE I'M CRAZY.
YOU SHOULD REALLY WANT TO
PRACTICE.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU SHOULD REALLY WANT US TO
PRACTICE,UN WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> I WANT US TO BE GOOD.
>> IF WE LOSE, SOMEONE IS GOING
HOME.
>> I THINK DRINKING WATER IS
ESSENTIAL, TOO.
IT'S WEIRD BEING THE ONLY GUY ON
THE TRIBE.
I HAVE TO BE PATIENT, MANAGE MY
MEXICOS, AND NOT GET TOO DOWN
AND TAKE MY SHOTS TO GET OUT OF
THIS TRIBE ALIVE.
I THINK THE PROBLEM IS IT'S
THREADING A LOT.
>> THAT WAS IT.
NO?
>> I THINK THE KEY IS A QUICK
RELEASE FROM THE THING.
>> DUDE, WHATEVER I DID WAS
PERFECT.
>> SO, LIKE-- NOPE.
>> A LITTLE HIGH.
>> I CAN WORK WITH IT IF IT'S
LOW.
♪ ♪ ♪
I DON'T LIKE THE HIGH ARC.
>> OH, GOOD.
>> YOU DEFINITELY DON'T WANT IT
TO TRAIL UP.
>> SORRY.
>> NOT IN THE FACE.
LOOK AT THE COCONUT.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE A TARGET.
YES.
I LIKE THE HAND TECHNIQUE.
EXACTLY.
YES.
>>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUY!
BRAWN AND BEAUTY TRIBE, GETTING
YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW BRAIN
TRIBE.
GARRETT VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, SHOCKED
REACTIONS.
ALL RIGHT, ARE YOU GUYS READY TO
GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
I'LL TAKE BACK THE IDOLS.
THAI.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO USE A BUCKET TO SCOOP
WATER FROM THE OCEAN.
YOU'LL THEN WORK TOGETHER
PASSING WATER FROM TRIBE MATE TO
TRIBE MATE, AND INTO A
CONTAINER.
WHEN THE CONTAINER FILLS, IT
WILL DROP, RELEASING A BALL.
TWO TRIBE MATES WILL THEN USE
THAT BALL TO SOLVE A VERTICAL
MAZE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE A THIRD PERSON WILL BE
VOTED OUT.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: GIVEN THE WEATHER
THIS WILL HELP A LOT.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH, COMFORT
AND SHELTER.
YOU HAVE BLANKETS.
PILLOWS.
MOSQUITO NET.
AND A TARP TO KEEP YOU DRY.
NO MATTER WHAT CONDITION YOUR
SHELTER IS IN, A TARP WILL
IMPROVE IT.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH, NO
COMFORT, BUT SHELTER IN THE FORM
OF A TARP.
>> OH, MY GOSH GRA.
>> Jeff: A LOT AT STAKE IN
THIS COLLEGE.
BRAWN, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
MEMBERS, WHO ARE YOU GOING TO
SIT OUT?
>> JEFF, ME AND LINDZ REGOING TO
SIT OUT.
>> Jeff: FOR THE BEAUTY TRIBE
YOU'RE SITTING OUT WHO PEOPLE.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE JEFRA AND
ALEXIS ARE GOING TO SIT THIS ONE
OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYONE ELSE, GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO STRATEGIZE, AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ALL ABOUT TEAM WORK.
>> NICE, GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: FIRST YOU GOTTA TOSS
THE BUCKET.
THEN YOU HAVE TO TOSS THE WATER.
WHATEVER WATER YOU GET, YOU'VE
GOT TO DUMP.
YOU'RE TRYING TO COLLECT AS MUCH
WATER AS YOU CAN WITH EACH PASS.
ONCE THAT CONTAINER FILLS, IT
WILL DROP, RELEASING THE BALL,
AND YOU'RE DONE WITH THIS PHASE.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: OUT OF THE GATE, IT
IS THE BEAUTY TRIBE IN THE LEAD.
BRAWN RIGHT BEHIND THEM.
AND THE BRAIN TRIBE IN LAST, AS
USUAL.
SPENCER DESPERATE TO CHANGE
SOMETHING FOR THE BRAIN TRIBE,
MOVING AS FAST AS HE CAN TO
TAWIVE AOVER TO J'TIA, WHO IS
GETTING DRENCHED.
VERY LITTLE OF THAT WATER MAKING
ITS WAY TO KASS.
BEAUTY TRIBE IS PULLING AWAY
WITH THIS ONE.
WHATEVER THEY'RE DOING IS
WORKING.
GREAT TOSS BY THE BRAWN TRIBE.
>> JUST TOSS IT!
>> Jeff: TASHA AND J'TIA STILL
HAVING TROUBLE COMMUNICATING.
BEAUTY GETTING CLOSER TO
FINISHING THIS FIRST PHASE.
BRAWN IN SECOND, BRAINS STILL IN
LAST.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT, YOU NEED
TO PICK, THIS, UP.
BEAUTY TRIBE VERY CLOSE.
MORGAN CAN SEE IT.
THIS MIGHT BE ENOUGH.
>> HERE WE GO!
>> Jeff: THAT DOES IT FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE!
START WORKING ON THE MAZE NOW.
IT IS NOW BETWEEN BRAWN AND
BRAIN FOR THAT SECOND SPOT.
BEAUTY TRIBE WORKING ON THE MAZE
NOW.
>> YOU FIRST, PULL, PULL, PULL.
>> Jeff: CLIFF WITH ANOTHER
BUCKET OF WATER, AND THAT WILL
DO IT FOR THE BRAWN TRIBE.
START WORKING ON THE MAZE, BRAWN
TRIBE.
KEEP MOVING, BRAIN TRIBE!
>> GO RIGHT OR LEFT?
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> Jeff: TWO TRIBES ARE
WORKING ON THE VERTICAL BRAZE,
THE BRAWN TRIBE AND THE BEAUTY
TRIBE, AND ONCE AGAIN THE BRAIN
TRIBE IS TRYING TO GET BACK IN
THE CHALLENGE AND THEY ARE NOT
VERY CLOSE.
>> AS SOON AS YOU GO DOWN, I'M
GOING TO YANK IT ON MY SIDE.
>> Jeff: YOU NEED TO WORK
TOGETHER TO MANEUVER THE BALL TO
THE OUTSIDE OF THE MAZE UNTIL
THE BALL DROPS.
>> THREE, TWO, ONE.
OKAY, GO BACK.
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE HAS YET
TO WIN, ONCE AGAIN, ABSOLUTELY
NO WATER IN THE BUCKET FROM
J'TIA TO KASS ON THAT.
BRAWN WITH A BIT OF A LEAD IN
THE VERTICAL MAZE, BUT BEAUTY
RIGHT THERE.
ALL YOU WANT TO DO IS MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T FINISH LAST.
BRAIN TRIBE GETTING CLOSER.
THAT WILL DO IT!
>> YES!
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE WORKING
ON THE MAZE NOW.
ANOTHER CHANCE FOR THEM TO LIVE
UP TO THEIR NAME.
BUT THE BRAWN AND BEAUTY TRIBE
HAVE HAD A LOT OF TIME TO WORK
ON THIS.
FIGURING OUT A COMPLICATED MAZE.
>> OH, NICE ONE!
>> Jeff: BRAWN GETTING CLOSER
NOW.
THEY FIGURED IT OUT.
THEY'RE ONE BIG MOVE AWAY FROM
WINNING IT.
THERE IT IS.
THAT COULD DO IT.
YES!
BRAWN WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE
MORE TRIBE.
BRAIN TRIBE IS BACK IN THIS.
>> OH!
>> DO IT AGAIN, DO IT AGAIN, YOU
DO IT.
>> Jeff: WORKING TOGETHER WELL
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THIS
CHALLENGE!
>> Jeff: ANOTHER GOOD MOVE BY
THE BRAIN TRIBE.
BEAUTY TRIBE NOW STRUGGLING.
THIS IS THE CLOSEST THE BRAIN
TRIBE HA HAS BEEN TO FINISHING.
WOULD BE A HUGE COMEBACK.
THE BEAUTY TRIBE IS FALLING
APART.
BRAIN TRIBE VERY CLOSE NOW, BIG
MOVE BY THE BRAIN TRIBE.
THAT WILL DO IT.
BRAIN TRIBE WINS IMMUNITY AND
REWARD!
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR THE FIRST
TIME THIS SEASON.
BRAWN TRIBE, CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY AGAIN.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND A NICE
REWARD.
( APPLAUSE )
BRAIN TRIBE, YOU'VE BEEN WAITING
A WHILE FOR THIS, YOUR FIRST
TASTE OF IMMUNITY.
WELL EARNED.
AND, ALSO, A TARP TO GO ALONG
WITH IT.
BRAWN TRIBE, COME GET YOUR
REWARD.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP AND ENJOY
ANOTHER NIGHT FREE OF TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
BRAIN TRIBE, COME GRAB YOUR
TARP.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL MISS YOU AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WE WON'T MISS YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BY THE
TRIBE, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU,
EXCEPT A DATE WITH ME TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE THIRD PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> HOME, SWEET HOME.
>> LOOK AT THIS CRAP.
SEE YOU LATER, PALM FRONDS.
>> WE KILLED THE CHALLENGE
AGAIN.
WE ALL KNOW HOW TO KEEP OUR
COMPOSURE WHEN YOU'RE UNDER
PRESSURE IN A COMPETITION.
>> WE'RE GOING TO BE WATER PROOF
RIGHT NOW.
>> WE'VE GOT THE TARP.
WE'VE GOT THE COMFORT.
I MEAN, YEAH, IT'S INSANE.
I FEEL LIKE A BRAND NEW PERSON,
LIKE, BRING ON THE RAIN.
>> WHEN WE BROUGHT BACK THE
COMFORT ITEMS FROM THE REWARD
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE I SAID THERE
MIGHT BE A POTENTIAL CLUE IN
THERE OR A POTENTIAL ATTORNEY
GENERAL VJ.
MY BRAIN IS TICKING WHILE THEIRS
IS NOT, I GUESS.
I TOOK THE HAMMOCK OFF TO THE
SIDE JUST IN CASE SOMETHING FELL
OUT, AND I OPENED IT, AND A
LITTLE PIECE OF PAPER THAT
LOOKED LIKE A CLUE FELL OUT AND
DROPPED ON THE FLOOR.
I IMMEDIATELY PUT MY FOOT RIGHT
ON TOP OF IT.
I LOOKED AROUND, NOBODY WAS
THERE.
I BEPT DOWN, PICKED IT UP, AND
PUT IT IN MY POCKET.
IT DIDN'T PERTAIN TO ANYTHING I
NEEDED BECAUSE I ALREADY HAVE
THE IDOL.
BUT I WANTED TO MAKE SURE IF
THERE WAS A CLUE IN THERE, I
WANTED TO GET MY HAPPENED ON IT.
I DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING EXWB ELSE
TO SEE IT.
>> THAT IS AWESOME, MAN.
>> CAN I GET IN THE HAMMOCK?
DOES ANYONE CARE?
>> I HOPE YOU FALL ON YOUR ASS.
>> AH!
( LAUGHTER )
>> OH, DREAMS DO COME TRUE IN
"SURVIVOR."
>> SORRY, GUYS.
>> WIN AS A TEAM, LOSE AS A
TEAM.
>> YOU GUYS WERE KILLING IT ON
THAT WATER, THOUGH.
GOOD JOB, MORGAN.
>> YOU GUYS WERE SO AHEAD.
>> I HATE MAKING EXCUSES.
WE DIDN'T GET IT DONE.
>> OUT HERE, YOU HAVE SO MANY
DIFFERENT ELEMENTS JUST HITTING
YOU AT ONCE.
>> BABY, STAY LIT, BABY, STAY
LIT.
>> WE WERE JUST IN THE MIDDLE OF
A HURRICANE.
WE LOST THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE SO EXHAUSTED.
AND NOW, WE'RE GOING TO TRIBAL.
I THINK THE ENERGY ON OUR BEACH
IS GOING TO RETURN REALLY DARK.
IT'S GOING TO TURN SUPER
NEGATIVE AND SUSPICIOUS.
>> IS ANYBODY READY TO GO HOME?
I MEAN, THAT'S A STUPID
QUESTION, BUT IN CASE ANYBODY
HAS HAD ENOUGH.
I FIGURED I'D ASK.
>> TONIGHT WE'VE GOT TO FINALLY
GO TO TRIBAL.
YOU KNOW, IT HAD TO HAPPEN
EVENTUALLY.
JEREMIAH, MYSELF, ALEXIS, AND
JEFRA ARE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE.
BETWEEN MORGAN AND BRICE, THE
ONE I'VE GOT TO WORRY ABOUT IS
BRICE.
HE SEEMS LIKE HE'S GOING TO BE
TOUGH TOWARDS THE END OF THE
GAME, AND IT'S THE BETTER MOVE
TO MAKE A MOVE ON BRICE NOW.
>> IT'S GONNA BE BRICE.
>> IF SOMETHING HAPPENS, IT'S
GOING TO BE BRICE.
>> I THINK SO, YEAH.
>> I DO WORRY THAT THE TRIBE MAY
COME TOGETHER AND SAY BRICE IS
REALLY MAYBE NOT A PHYSICAL
THREAT BUT BRICE IS DEFINITELY A
SOCIAL THREAT.
SO THEY MAY TARGET ME, BUT I
TRUST IN JEREMIAH.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
ON THE SAME PAGE TO GET A GIRL
OUT TONIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU REALLY THINKING?
>> I MEAN, I'M REALLY THINKING
ALEXIS, BUT WHAT-- DID L.J. SAY
ANYTHING TO YOU?
>> NOT REALLY.
I MEAN HE'S THINKING-- THINKING
YOU.
>> IF IT'S ME NHE'S GOING TO
TARGET YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> L.J. THINKS HE HAS AN
ALLIANCE OF ALEXIS, JEFRA,
JEREMIAH, AND HIMSELF.
BUT IN REALITY, JEREMIAH'S WITH
BRICE AND I.
>> SURE DIDN'T THINK WE'D BE
GOING TO TRIBAL TONIGHT.
>> IT SUCKS, MAN.
>> I NEED TO TALK TO HER.
>> TONIGHT FOR THE VOTE, WE JUST
ARHAVE TO GET JEFRA IN THERE WIH
US TO MAKE THAT 4-2 VOTE.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WE'RE GONNA VOTE ALEXIS AND
WE WANT YOU TO DO IT WITH US.
AND I KNOW YOU GUYS ARE LIKE
REALLY GOOD FRIENDS BUT--
>> WELL, WHY DON'T WE VOTE OUT
L.J. OVER ALEXIS?
>> BECAUSE WE STILL NEED L.J.
FOR CHALLENGES.
>> JEREMIAH WILL TALK TO YOU.
>> WHEN DID YOU TALK TO
JEREMIAH?
>> PAST FEW DAYS.
>> OKAY.
>> AND HE'S IN ON THAT?
>> L.J. THINKS JEREMIAH'S PART
OF HIS ALLIANCE.
>> MORGAN AND JEREMIAH AND BRICE
HAVE AN ALLIANCE.
AND ARE GOING TO BE VOTING FOR
ALEXIS TONIGHT.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
IS JEREMIAH WITH ME AND ALEXIS
AND L.J. OR WITH BRICE AND
MORGAN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S JUST WHAT WE WERE
THINKING.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> MAYBE I'LL GET A CHANCE TO
TALK TO JEREMIAH.
>> UH-HUH, I'LL HAVE JEREMIAH
TALK TO YOU.
>> PEOPLE ARE THROWING OUT
STRATEGIES I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
BEFORE.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST ABSOLUTELY
NUTS.
I'M NOT EXCITED ABOUT TONIGHT,
BECAUSE I THINK SOMEBODY IS
REALLY GOING TO GET BLINDSIDED.
>> MORGAN JUST CAME UP TO ME AND
SAID ALL KINDS OF CRAZY STUFF.
>> WHAT DID SHE SAY?
>> SHE SAID YOU'RE IN AN
ALLIANCE WITH HER AND BRICE AND
YOU AND BRICE AND HER WERE ALL
VOTING FOR ALEXIS.
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
>> SO WE'RE STILL GOOD WITH OUR
ORIGINAL PLAN?
>> WE'RE STILL GOOD.
>> ME, YOU, L.J., AND-- ME, YOU,
L.J., AND ALEXIS VOTING FOR
BRICE.
>> YES.
ARE ME AND YOU STILL--
>> YEAH, I'M STILL GOOD.
>> JEFRA DOES NOT WANT TO VOTE
AGAINST ALEXIS.
>> BRICE AND MORGAN IS VOTING
ALEXIS.
SO I'M KIND OF-- I MEAN, I'M
STUCK.
IS THERE ANY DANGER IN SPLITTING
IT?
>> I DON'T THINK THERE IS.
IF WE SPLIT IT 2-2 AND THEY HAVE
2 FOR SOMEBODY.
>> THEN IT'S A THREE-WAY TIE.
>> AND THEN YOU REVOTE.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS.
>> AND IF NO ONE PLAYS AN IDOL,
WE ALL VOTE FOR ONE PERSON.
RIGHT NOW, I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANY DANGER IN SPLITTING IT.
>> WHO SHOULD WE--
>> I SAY THE GIRLS FOR BRICE,
BOYS FOR MORGAN.
>> MAYBE BRICE OR MORGAN HAVE A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
WHAT WE'RE ANYTHING TO DO IS
SPLIT THE VOTE.
THE TWO BOYS ARE GOING TO VOTE
FOR MORGUE AN AND THE TWO GIRLS
ARE GOING TO VOTE FOR BRICE.
IF NEITHER ONE HAS AN IDOL, A
TIE EQUALS A REVOTE AND WE'LL
ALL VOTE FOR BRICE.
>> THERE'S ALWAYS THE FEAR OF
THIS IDOL BEING PLAYED.
IF I CAN GET MY MAJORITY TO MAKE
A SPLIT VOTE, WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE A THREE-WAY TIE AND IT'S
GOING TO PUT ME ABSOLUTE IN THE
MIDDLE.
>> YEAH, WE CAN DO THAT.
>> FIGO WITH BRICE AND MORGAN, I
COULD GET RID OF ALEXIS.
MY MAIN GOAL IS TO TAKE OVER
THIS TRIBE, AND I'M GOING TO
HAVE NUMBERS IS WHAT I'M REALLY
HOPING FOR.
>> MAKE SURE YOU VOTE FOR
ALEXIS, PLEASE.
I'M NOT WORRIED TONIGHT BECAUSE
I DO TRUST IN JEREMIAH AND
MORGAN.
>> OUR FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL, I
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO EXPECT.
>> AND I THINK JEFRA FEELS WAY
MORE COMFORTABLE WITH JEREMIAH
THAN L.J. SO ALLIANCES ARE GOING
TO BE EXPOSED AND PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO BE PUT IN THEIR PLACE.
>> I'VE GOT A BIG DECISION ON MY
HANDS TONIGHT.
I COULD GO WITH L.J., ALEXIS,
AND JEFRA OR BRICE AND MORGAN.
GOING INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL
KNOWING I HAVE ALL THE POWER IS
AN AMAZING FEELING.
I AM JUST A COUNTRY GUY.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT SOMEBODY'S
FEELINGS BUT AFTER THIS VOTE I'M
GOING TO HURT SOMEONE'S FEELINGS
AND SMNL IS GOING TO LOSE THEIR
TRUST IN ME AND THAT'S GOING TO
HURT ME MORE THAN ANYTHING.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
MORGAN, LET'S TALK ABOUT HOW YOU
ARE GROUPED TOGETHER AS THE
BEAUTIFUL TRIBE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: ARE THERE ANY OTHER
CLICHES ASSOCIATED WITH BEAUT
THEY YOU THINK THIS TRIBE
EMBODIED?
>> I MEAN, YEAH, WE'VE GOT
GOOD-LOOK FACES.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I LIKE IT.
SORRY, THERE'S A BUG IN MY HAIR.
>> Jeff: BRICE, HOW DID YOU
FEEL WHEN YOU FOUND OUT YOU WERE
GROUPED IN WITH THE BEAUTIFUL
TRIBE?
>> I WAS EXCITED.
I LOOK AT MYSELF AS, YOU KNOW,
BEAUTIFUL.
AND THAT COMES WITH AN INNER
STRENGTH.
IT COMES WITH THINGS THAT YOU'VE
GONE THROUGH IN YOUR LIFE TO
HAVE THE BUTTERFLY EFFECT WHERE
YOU CAN COME OUT OF THE
CATERPILLAR AND BE A BEAUTIFUL
BUTTERFLY.
I FEEL LIKE I'M AT THE BUTTERFLY
STAGE OF MY LIFE FLYING AROUND
AND LOOK PRETTY.
>> Jeff: JEFRA, TELL ME ABOUT
THE FIRST FEW DAYS OUT HERE.
>> WELL, THE FIRST COUPLE OF
DAYS AROUND OUR TRIBE IT WAS
ACTUALLY, LIKE, ONE BIG PARTY,
JEFF.
WE WERE LIKE A GROUP OF COLLEGE
FRIENDS.
ALL THESE BEAUTIFUL KIDS OUT
HERE HANGING OUT.
AND THEN THE STORM CAME, AND
THAT CHANGED EVERYBODY'S
ATTITUDE AND MOMENTUM.
AND WE LOST THE CHALLENGE TODAY,
AND EVERYBODY'S PARANOID BECAUSE
UP UNTIL THIS POINT, NOBODY THAT
I WAS AWARE OF HAD REALLY TALKED
STRATEGY.
>> Jeff: BRICE, HOW ABOUT YOU?
DID YOU SENSE THAT PARANOIA THIS
AFTERNOON?
>> I MEAN, I THINK EVERYONE IS
CONCERNED ABOUT TONIGHT BUT
THERE HAVE BEEN TALKS AROUND
CAMP.
YOU KNOW, THERE HAVE BEEN CLEAR
FORMATION OF PEOPLE.
YOU CAN SEE JEREMIAH AND L.J.
THERE TOGETHER.
YOU WORRY ABOUT ALEXIS AND JEFRA
TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, AND SOMETIMES THEY GET
TOGETHER AS A FOUR SELL.
THAT LEAVES MYSELF AND MORGAN
OUT.
>> Jeff: IF YOU AND MORGAN ARE
ON THE OUTSIDE, TELL ME WHERE
BTHE WAY YOU MIGHT BE CONCERNED.
>> THERE IS A LOT OF TALKING
AMONGST EVERYONE, BUT THERE ARE
CERTAIN PEOPLE THAT EVAPORATE
TALKED STRATEGICS WITH ME AT
ALL.
>> Jeff: WHO?
>> I WOULD SAY ALEXIS.
SHE HASN'T TALKED TO ME AT ALL
ABOUT ALLIANCES.
SO I'M PRETTY SURE SHE'S GUNNING
FOR ME.
>> Jeff: SO IS IT A FORGONE
CONCLUSION YOU'RE VOTING FOR
ALEXIS?
>> JEFF, I FEEL LIKE EVERYONE
SHOULD PULL THEIR OWN WEIGHT
AROUND CAMP, YOU KNOW.
>> Jeff: DOT, DOT, DOT.
>> DOT, DOT, DOT.
>> Jeff: ALEXIS, HOW DOES THAT
SIT WITH YOU? DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE PULLING YOUR OWN WEIGHT?
>> I MEAN, HEENES THE GAME.
HE CAN TOTALLY USE THAT TO TRY
TO BE AMMO TO GET ME OUT.
I LOVE BRICE.
>> AND LOVE BEING AROUND HIM.
I HOPE THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
BUT IT COULD POSSIBLY HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: BRICE HAS THERE BEEN
ANY TALK ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
IDOLS ARE PLAYING A PART IN THIS
GAME?
>> THERE HAS BEEN TALK THAT
PEOPLE COULD POSSIBLY HAVE
IDOLS.
THERE'S TALK OF THE TOWN THAT
MORGAN, SINCE SHE'S THE FIRST
PERSON AT OUR CAMP, THAT SHE HAS
AN IDOL.
SO I KNOW THERE'S TALK OF THE
TOWN THAT THERE ARE POSSIBLE
IDOLS IN PLAY.
>> Jeff: MORGAN, WITH ALL THE
TALK OF THE TOWN ABOUT IDOLS,
HOW DOES THAT SIT WITH YOU?
>> I'M A LITTLE CONCERNED,
ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, I THINK I KNOW WHERE
IT'S GOING IF EVERYTHING GOES
THE WAY, YOU KNOW, WE KIND OF
PLANNED IT TODAY.
BUT PEOPLE CAN, YOU KNOW, GO
BEHIND YOUR BACK AND BACKSTAB
YOU AND YOU DON'T EVEN SEE IT.
>> Jeff: SO, JEREMIAH, WE'VE
ESTABLISHED THAT BRICE, MORGAN,
AND ALEXIS, ALL THREE FEEL A BIT
CONCERNED.
WHERE ARE YOU IN TERMS OF
THINKING YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN TONIGHT?
>> IT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH,UN.
I THINK I KNOW WHERE IT'S GOING,
BUT IT'S GOING-- IT'S GOING TO
HURT.
IT'S GOING TO SUCK, YOU KNOW.
BUT IT'S "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELL, IT
SEEMS LIKE THERE IS A LOT OF
UNCERTAINTY IN THIS TRIBE.
LET'S PUT AN END TO THAT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MORGAN, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTE ARE
READ THE DECISION IT FIND.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ALEXIS.
BRICE.
MORGAN.
ONE VOTE ALEXIS, ONE VOTE BRICE,
ONE VOTE MORGAN.
ALEXIS.
THAT'S TWO VOTES ALEXIS.
BRICE.
TWO VOTES BRICE, TWO VOTES
ALEXIS, ONE VOTE MORGAN, ONE
VOTE LEFT.
MORGAN.
WE HAVE A TIE.
ALEXIS, MORGAN, AND BRICE, YOU
WILL NOT VOTE.
L.J., JEFRA, JEREMIAH, YOU WILL
REVOTE AND YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR
ONE OF THESE THREE.
L.J., YOU'RE UP.
YOU'LL COME GRAB THIS
.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, BRICE.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN," BRICE.
THAT'S TWO.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
BRICE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> Jeff: WELL, IN LOSING YOUR
FIRST CHALLENGE AND VOTING OUT
YOUR FIRST MEMBER, YOU'VE GOTTEN
YOUR FIRST TASTE OF HOW THIS
GAME IS REALLY PLAYED.
THE QUESTION IS HOW QUICKLY WILL
YOU RECOVER.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> WE CAN EASILY THROW THIS.
>> Jeff: THE BRAWP TRIBE IS
LOOKING TO BLINDSIDE ONE OF
THEIR OWN.
>> SO LET'S JUST THROW IT TODAY.
LET'S GET HIM OUT.
>> Jeff: AND ONE CHALLENGE
LEAVES EVERYONE A LITTLE BANGED
UP.
>> UH-OH!
>> OH!
>> AAH!
>> Jeff: THAT'S GONNA LEAVE A
MARK.
>> I DEFINITELY AM A LITTLE
UPSET WITH JEREMIAH.
HE DEFINITELY KIND OF BETRAYED
BY TRUST.
BUT I'M SURE HE DOESN'T REALLY
UNDERSTAND WHAT HAPPENED.
I'M SURPRISED HE CAN EVEN SPELL
MY NAME.
BUT CLEARLY THEY WANTED THE
CUTEST MOST FASHIONABLE MEMBER
OUT FIRST AND I'M GLAD TO TAKE
THAT TITLE WITH BELLS AND
WHISTLES ON.
I HOPE MORGAN DOES WELL.
THE REST OF THE PEOPLE I DON'T
REMEMBER THEIR NAMES.