แปลจากภาษาอังกฤษ translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Throw away your bandanas.
After a surprise change,
Muscle, Intelligence
and Beauty were gone.
They were divided into two tribes,
the new Solana tribe
and the new Aparri tribe.
I am the only
original Aparri in the tribe,
with three members of Intelligence
and three of Beauty.
Chez Aparri ...
Our sweet home!
The former Beauty members
began to split.
At first, Jeremiah was with us,
then he switched sides, and switched again.
LJ and Alexis cuddle
every night.
Are you and Alexis friends?
We were at the start.
LJ, her and I, we were like that.
And the elders of Intelligence
took advantage of this to take control.
The fact that they're so divided
shows that they can be played
against each other.
While in Solana...
What a beautiful shelter!
Former
Muscle members relished
a 5 to 2 advantage
over LJ and Jefra.
If we continue with the people we have,
we are in a very good position.
But they could not
settle all the quarrels.
Trish makes me sick.
You're 50, stop trying to get
the attention of 20-year-old men.
And at the last immunity test...
Big win for the underdogs!
Solana destroys.
How it happened?
As the board approached,
the Muscle alumni took aim at LJ.
The four of us will vote for LJ.
- First?
- Light!
But Trish and Tony saw it as a chance
to eliminate a much bigger threat.
Cliff is very influential,
which makes it very dangerous.
And at tribal council,
Trish and Tony's wish was granted.
Cliff and his allies
were taken by surprise.
Cliff, the tribe has spoken.
There are thirteen left,
who will be eliminated tonight?
I would just like to
clarify some points,
because I think
it's really important,
I mean, Lindsey, I...
- Stop it, Trish.
- I'm talking.
- Come back down to Earth, Trish.
- Excuse me, I'm talking.
We took Cliff
completely by surprise.
He was so sure he was
n't leaving tonight.
You completely screwed up.
And who do you think you're allied with?
- I'm out of wedding rings.
- No, indeed.
His alliance
was Lindsey and Cliff, period.
We got rid of Cliff
and she finds herself alone.
- Let me explain to you.
- OK.
In the future, I will respect you,
because this team is moving forward.
But I don't love you.
You know what? You disgust me.
Everything about you is annoying.
Your laughter, your teeth, your face...
Everything you are,
I can't stand it.
So why not step
back a little bit,
shut up, and don't
talk to me for a while?
So you're telling us
you're not on the team?
I'm not on your team,
I never will be.
You're annoying, scary,
and maybe the worst person
- that I have ever met.
- Do you find me annoying?
- Yes I think so.
- OK.
Now
ask me if I'm interested.
I don't care if you're interested.
It's the best. I can leave
and never think about you again.
Alright, that's enough. It's finish.
We all know what
to expect now.
Let's just try to live
with it, that's all.
Trish started
to take it out on me.
She is tyrannical, and she has
her mouth in the ass of a horse.
And emotionally, I'm
not sure I can handle it.
- I can't stay in the same...
- I'm sorry Cliff left.
I know you will miss him.
And I'm sorry about that.
I don't want to
play this with Trish.
So I'll take
what's left of my sanity,
and I'll have to figure
out what to do next,
because I won't do that,
I won't stay near his mouth.
Yo, we have no idea
where Lindsey is, man.
And it's cold, and it's night.
I hope she's okay, man.
I hope she
's just licking her wounds.
She's not used
to being in the cold like this.
- Hey, Lindsey.
- Hi.
I was told you wanted to talk.
What is happening?
As soon as we got back to camp,
Trish got wild on me
with his dirty mouth.
What was she telling you?
Horrible and ridiculous things.
I can't live like this anymore.
At this point, I can't let
anyone upset me that much.
- What do you think will happen?
- I'm going to fall on him.
That's why
I walked away.
I'd rather give up
the million dollars
I'd rather my daughter see
me behaving like that.
So it's just
between you and Trish.
It's just a clash of personalities.
But it's so extreme...
and I'm cold, I'm wet, I'm hungry,
I know it, and I'm tired.
I realize it, and I know
I'm going to regret it.
I need the million
more than anyone here.
But I can honestly say
I can't take it anymore.
Are you giving up?
I don't know what else to do.
I have to say this is a first.
No one has ever
given up out of fear
to do something
he might regret,
and after reflection, decided
it was best to retire.
It makes me really sad.
It was hard for me.
What was the hardest?
When I leave this beach,
it will be the hardest moment.
How should
the tribe be notified?
I would like to act responsibly
and explain my departure to them,
but it would be better
if I stayed a little here,
out of politeness, then I leave.
Hello everyone.
Oh, it's Jeff.
- Everyone awake?
- Yes.
I have information
to give you.
Lindsey was gone,
was everything okay?
She left in her underwear,
and even though I don't like her,
I don't want her to get hurt.
I still care about her.
I'm just here to
officially inform you
that after losing Cliff,
which was apparently a surprise,
Lindsey retires from the game.
I feel bad,
because I took it out on her,
but she has become
disagreeable, mean.
Then she left,
and I'm not surprised
that she gives up, as she
cannot live without Cliff.
As expected.
Turn your head, the body will follow.
She was the body and Cliff the head.
She followed him to the exit.
That's wonderful.
Two for the price of one.
It was an explosive situation,
unstable, and when it popped...
Now we're cool.
It's as if we could
start off on the right foot.
Here we are, the five solids.
Before the council, I was allied
with Cliff and Lindsey.
That they are gone
puts me in an awkward position.
If we go to tribal council,
I could totally see myself leaving.
Survivor - Season 28 Episode 6
We Found Our Zombies
Over here, everyone!
Aparri, discover
the new Solana tribe.
Cliff was eliminated
at last night's council.
A few hours later,
Lindsey gave up.
- What?
- My God.
She retired from the game
for personal reasons.
Sarah, you can't
help yourself.
Oh my God!
This is... insane.
Alexis, I'm surprised
by the reaction, what's up?
I'm glad to see...
our beauties still standing.
I'm happy, of course.
Spencer, you nod. "It's good.
Good news, yeah. I love it."
Two people left
without me having to do anything.
It bothers me that someone gives up,
I really don't like it,
but I'll take it.
My chances improved
and I didn't have to do anything.
And here is the Solana tribe
reduced to five members.
Aparri en a 7.
And the game has changed
again.
- Ready for today's challenge?
- Yes.
Today you will
face each other one on one.
Each will carry an idol.
Knock down
the opponent's idol
before he
drops yours.
If you succeed, you score
a point for your tribe.
The first team to four
wins the reward.
- Want to know what's at stake?
- Yes.
Two members of the winning tribe will
accompany the losers
and plunder their camp.
This is an opportunity
to improve your camp life
- and inflict heavy damage.
- We must not be looted.
Aparri, you are two more,
two will not participate.
It can't be the same
twice in a row.
Who will not participate?
Alexis and Kass.
Take a seat on the bench. The others,
a minute to get organized.
And we'll start.
Let's go!
Man against man.
Spencer launches against Woo.
Go-y, Woo!
It is very simple.
Take down his idol before
he takes down yours,
and you score a point.
- We play in 4 points.
- Go ahead, Spence!
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
- Go ahead, Spence!
- Take it easy, Woo.
Woo smiles, provoking Spencer!
You got it, Woo.
Use your focus. Ninja!
It's a duel at the top.
Who will attack first?
Spencer closes in,
provoking Woo in turn!
Keep the balance, Woo!
Spencer gives it a shot and succeeds!
Aparri scores and leads 1 to 0!
Well done, Spencer.
Next round.
It's Trish, for Solana,
against Tasha, for Aparri.
Survivors, ready?
- Go-y Tasha.
- Allez, Tasha.
Are you going to play
aggressive or defensive?
- Tasha launches.
- Go-y Tasha.
Can we hit each other?
Trish pushes her away like a bug.
Don't hit her too hard, Trish.
Tasha rushes at her.
Tasha goes for a big shot,
but misses!
Trish scores for Solana.
Tied, 1-1.
Sarah against Jefra.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Sarah rushes at Jefra.
It's okay, my sister.
- It's very aggressive.
- Keep the balance!
She can't reach it,
Jefra protects her. Nope!
Sarah succeeds.
Aparri scores and leads.
Appearance 2, Solana
Next round.
Jeremiah versus LJ.
Go ahead, LJ.
Confrontation of bearded mountaineers.
You'll get it, Jeremiah.
Aparri leads 2-1, we play in 4.
Go LJ!
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Come on, Jeremiah!
LJ would like to equalize.
Lots of action.
You got it, you got it!
He tries to recover
but Jeremiah can't!
Solana score!
Tied, 2-2.
The next round will be mixed.
Morgan will face Tony.
Come on, buddy.
An inequality due
to the division of the tribes.
- You'll get there, Morgan.
- Come on, Morgan.
Don't look her
in the eye, bro.
Because you're going to be distracted?
- Directly.
- Lord.
Let's go.
2-2, we play in 4.
Survivors, ready?
Tony against Morgan, he goes after her.
Morgan charges at him,
but Morgan lets go first.
Solana scores and leads 3-2.
We go back to the beginning.
We replay the first game.
- Come on, Spencer.
- This could be the end.
- Come on, Woo.
- Spencer and Woo.
Come on, Wooo.
Woo could bring
victory to Solana.
- Keep the distance.
- Spencer must win,
for Aparri to remain competitive.
Spencer won the first time.
We can go visit
our old tribe.
- Feed the family, kid.
- Come on Spence, we can't lose.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
You'll get it, Spencer.
Woo goes straight for Spencer.
Spencer has a great reach.
- In style, Woo.
- Woo don't move.
It's getting closer.
There you are, Woo. Unbalance it.
Keep your feet moving, Woo.
Unbalance it, Woo. So!
Nice move from Woo,
but Spencer hangs on.
- You got it, Spencer.
- Let him come.
Spencer doesn't back down.
Another duel at the top
between these two.
It's okay, Woo.
Woo go for it and succeed!
Solana wins the reward!
Solana, congratulations.
You will choose two people
who will accompany Aparri
to their camp.
Who are you going to choose?
OK. Here is a message.
Don't open it until
you're at their beach.
Then read it together,
apart.
It will tell you what to do.
- OK?
- Very well.
Tony, Woo, join this tribe.
See you soon!
Tony, you have a very good
idea of ​​what Aparri has.
I know Aparri like the back of my hand,
Jeff, that's why I'm going.
Trish, Jefra, LJ, get
your things and head back to camp.
And wait
for your companions to return with their loot.
Take your things. Go for it.
The afternoon
should be interesting.
There's so much more energy at camp
since Cliff and Lindsey left.
We showed them that we are
in the minority, but that we have morals.
They saw it, and we won.
We lost
the reward trial,
and today
the reward is plunder.
So when Tony and Woo came,
our hearts stopped.
Welcome to the house.
Thanks thanks.
Like Jeff said, we'll
read that over there and come back.
OK.
I come from Luzon,
we lived there rather badly.
Arriving in Aparri,
we thought we were in luxury.
Who would have thought
it would last so short?
You can take two
of these items from the Aparri tribe.
2 blankets, 2 pillows, 1 hammock.
That's more or less
all we wanted.
Or the tarp and the rope,
or the fishing kit.
- What do you want? Number 1?
- Numbers 1 and 3.
- OK.
- We can weaken them with the tarp...
- No matter.
- OK.
After we won,
Jeff gave us instructions.
The second part of the instructions
was a clue about the idol.
"Walk along the rocks.
It's easier at low tide.
Spend some time near the reef,
and you could be protected tonight."
This is for us, huh?
It is for us.
Woo and I read it, and it
doesn't match Aparri beach,
it corresponds to Solana beach,
where we have a wall of rocks.
"Choose someone...
...to fetch an idol",
to confuse them?
On choisit Jeremiah,
they will all believe that
Jeremiah has a clue about the idol.
- OK.
- And they'll want to fire him.
That's good.
It would be great to oust
one of them, put the bronx on.
And the strongest
Aparri is Jeremiah.
We'll take the comfort
and the fishing kit.
And we have a clue
about the immunity idol.
And we have to choose
who to give it to.
We decided
to give it to Jeremiah.
OK? So we're going to go there.
The comfort and the fishing kit.
Tony and Woo decided
to give Jeremiah
a clue about the hidden idol.
So I think they're sending
a signal to Jeremiah:
"we want to team up with you".
Here is the clue.
Read it alone, and then
do what you want with it. OK?
- And we want the fishing net.
- Yeah.
So I gave him the hint.
And I'm sure at that moment
everyone was thinking:
"Why does Jeremiah have the clue?
What's going on?".
They must already
be thinking.
"Oh, oh! He's going to find the idol,
blah blah blah."
"Walk along the rocks.
It's easier at low tide.
Spend time near the reef..."
I opened the index and read it.
It's actually the same clue
we got at the Beauty tribe.
The chosen.
For I don't know what reason.
"It's a joke".
Tony and Woo
don't even know me.
"We have a clue about the idol,
and we choose
to give it to Jeremiah".
See you next time.
I got six people
watching me
and who will watch me closely.
I could be
the next eliminated.
I have to take the clue again.
If he shows it to them, they'll see
it wasn't for them.
Shame on YOU, Lindsie.
Hello.
Got a bag of rice?
The message told us
what we could take.
- Couldn't you have rice?
- Nope.
- Did you take the salt and pepper?
- Absolutely.
- You will love this.
- Do you have the frying pan?
You riz free!
We have traps.
Tony and Woo brought back
lots of comfort items.
A mosquito net, pillows,
blankets...
Spices, salt and pepper.
Things that LJ and I have
n't been able to enjoy since the beginning.
That's the best part.
- That's a clue for the idol.
- Here?
At first, we thought
it was for them.
But that's not the case.
It's about a rock wall.
This wall of rocks.
I told them
that this message was asking us
to choose a person among them
to give him the clue.
We called Jeremiah.
And we put a big,
conspicuous target on his back.
Tony has been playing hard from the start.
He doesn't back down from anything.
He lies, steals and cheats.
And I'm just glad
he's on my side.
And I have something else to tell you.
I am a police officer.
- I was kidding for the construction.
- I knew it.
- That's smart.
- Is it a joke?
No, it's serious.
13 days with the old Aparri,
and I felt nothing for them.
Not the slightest feeling.
Except for Trish.
But in the new Solana,
we bonded, it's harmonious.
Tony, I'm impressed.
You are talented. You got me good.
I'm gullible, but you got me.
To prove
that he is trustworthy,
Tony disclosed that he had lied.
It's different.
Since you also have a son,
I was always going to swear on mine.
I didn't see him as a smart guy.
But he's quick-witted,
he's no fool.
Truly not.
I realized,
when he exposed all of this,
that I must be constantly
on my guard.
We stay together. The five.
I love you more now
than an hour ago.
You will wonder
if I am lying. How to believe me?
But that, you can
believe in it until the end.
- Yeah.
- Until the end.
I have to tell you something.
I am a man.
I knew it!
Tony and Woo told us
that they had a clue
about our immunity idol,
and that they could
share it with one person.
They chose Jeremiah,
which made everyone think.
It really rocked the camp.
So I have to
clarify some things.
Because for me, right now, Jeremiah
is the least trustworthy.
Jeremiah is so unpredictable.
He's so stupid
he can't lie.
It sounded like Alexis had
planned out what she was going to say.
Which suggests she might
be playing us a bit.
And I think she's a little smarter
than she likes to show off.
What worries me is that
I have seven, and I'm not one.
Yeah.
It's the five over there,
Jeremiah and Sarah.
I like girls who assume
their intelligence and their abilities.
Alexis is rather hypocritical.
I think it plays against her.
No way to trust him for a shot.
Why did they give it
to you instead of Sarah?
Let me ask you
a question. We lost.
We lost.
Why would we receive a hint?
What happened
is that they want...
Are you saying that's not a clue?
Not a new one.
It's the same one we had at camp.
Exactly the same.
- What? It's absurd.
- Exactly the same.
I read it.
The clue Tony gave me
is the same as we had
in the other tribe.
He said he had to take it back.
So I gave it back to him.
Tony fooled me.
Now
I have to get out of here.
You say they came
with their clue?
Yes, to call me
in front of everyone,
- make everyone think...
- You're paranoid.
- Who?
- You.
No, they want
you all to vote against me.
I'm not paranoid.
Jeremiah's story
is hard to swallow.
I think Jeremiah
got a new clue.
He was thrilled,
it was a new clue.
He looked real.
And it sounded like a clue
to an idol that's here.
He does not deceive anyone.
Over here, everyone!
- Ready for the immunity test?
- Yes.
First of all, Tasha, I'm getting her back.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will build
a staircase with wooden posts.
You will pass through
a bamboo maze.
Go down a slide.
A person will move
a key along a string.
The key will release a machete.
You will use it to release
puzzle pieces.
Two team members will use it
to solve a puzzle,
which will reveal the three numbers
of a combination.
The first tribe to find
the code and release their flag
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
Losers, you know:
tribal council, someone will leave.
Apparri, you have two
more people. Who will not participate?
It can't be the same
two events in a row.
Morgan and Tash do not participate.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, one minute to
get organized, and we'll begin.
Let's go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Come on, Appari!
Build a staircase.
The small parts in front,
the large ones behind.
When it's over, go up,
and go through the maze.
LJ sinks into the mud.
It rained, the course is hard.
Be really careful
where you step.
Solana does anything.
They have large rooms
in front of smaller ones.
Help me take it off.
Get this one out, get this one out!
Aparri succeeds first.
Appari climbs.
Solana is still trying
to put it together.
Come on, Appari!
Very bad start for Solana.
Now you can go.
Go through the maze,
follow the path.
If it's blocked,
you can't pass.
Find the opening.
Come on, Appari!
Good collaboration at Solana.
Good collaboration at Aparri.
Well done, Sarah!
Sarah unties the knot for Aparri.
Woo unties the knot.
Woo untied the knot for Solana.
Woo is downstairs.
Sarah has untied the knot.
You go-y!
- Go on!
- Slip!
It's neck and neck.
Three are down for Aparri.
Everyone descended
in both tribes.
A person must now
take care of the key.
It's Tony for Solana,
Jeremiah for Aparri.
Come on, Jeremiah!
There you are, Tony.
That's good, Jeremiah!
Once at the end, release this key,
and with it the machete.
You and it's presque, Jeremiah.
Jeremiah released his key.
Untie that machete!
Tony is right behind.
Jeremiah released the machete.
Tony released his key.
Jeremiah released the coins.
Cross all!
Tony still takes care of the padlock.
Let two people put
the puzzle pieces together!
Two only!
Tony is wasting a
lot of his tribe's time.
Tony has the machete.
He released the coins.
Everyone must cross.
Now go!
Aparri has already gathered
all the pieces.
Looks like...
You build
this puzzle from the bottom up.
You are looking for three numbers.
These three numbers
will form your combination.
A big immunity at stake.
It's a four.
This one, hey!
Aparri begins to progress.
We're looking for a 41.
Turn it.
Like that? No that's not it.
Put it there!
LJ and Woo argue
over where the rooms are.
LJ is sure he's right.
If his numbers don't match,
they'll be wrong.
You might come across a piece
that looks right but isn't.
Make sure you're right.
4 or 67.
Both tribes look
for the second number.
- What's a number?
- 67.
That's it?
Flip it!
LJ and Woo now try
another combination.
They go back
and start over.
LJ thinks he has understood
something.
That's it.
No that's not it.
If that's so.
Aparri is still arguing
about this second number.
LJ places another piece.
And another.
Solana places another piece.
- They're still downstairs, calm down.
- Solana places two more pieces.
Aparri begins to panic,
they are left behind.
It takes a 67, come on!
They think it's good.
Big fall for LJ.
If it's right, it'll open
the padlock, and that's immunity.
It's just!
Solana wins immunity!
The top five!
The top five, baby!
Solana, congratulations.
Take it, Woo.
Big immunity.
No tribal council for Solana.
Pack your things, head back
to camp, enjoy your free evening.
Apparri, one of you is leaving.
Pack your things, get back to camp,
see you tonight at council.
"Yeah! Top five!
We're the bottom five!",
and I counted
five people in front.
And I was not.
I think that's telling.
I am not part
of their plans for the future.
So I'm going to go ahead
and create a new alliance.
Today,
it's bad luck, we lost.
And that sucks,
because we have to go to the council.
And I hate advice.
It's the worst place in the world.
Tony made a stupid mistake
by shouting "top five".
- Yeah.
- That was ridiculous.
Yeah, that was stupid.
Because we are seven at the moment,
and we will be six tomorrow.
After the ordeal,
Solana rejoiced,
and Tony openly shouted
"top five".
"Top Five, Baby!"
How do you say it
in New Jersey?
- "Yeah baby!"
- "Top five, Jeff!"
"Top Five, Baby!"
- "Look at my muscles, still there!"
- "Top five!"
Their confidence
was very telling.
It escapes me.
How to think of being the top five
by being a minority?
Minority.
They must think that one of the new
Aparri will join them after the merger.
The only one of our tribe
to have spoken to them is Jeremiah.
So I think they believe
Jeremiah is their sixth.
Jeremiah worries me.
They were excited about their top five.
They wouldn't do this
without having someone else.
- Yeah.
- And they only spoke to Jeremiah.
They shared the clue with him and...
Morgan and I, we know
he'll give you his word,
but that it will
not be sincere, that he will lie.
Alexis tried to convince us
of the need to eliminate Jeremiah.
She wants to persuade us
that he will change sides.
- I think we're in agreement.
- It's the safest thing.
- So it's safe, Jeremiah?
- Yeah.
And you give us your word.
I swear on everything...
Look,
no fingers crossed, no nothing.
I will not betray.
We believe you.
Intelligence can go
both ways at this point.
In the event of a merger,
retaining Jeremiah is risky.
This is to determine
the greatest risk.
Both have opposite ties.
The two could
make deals against us.
We'll say yes to Alexis' plan,
we'll tell him that eliminating
Jeremiah by surprise is fine with us.
Then we will decide
what really suits us.
I wonder what steps
to take towards the merger.
For tonight, it seems
Intelligence is in control.
Everybody knows
we three are strong,
and that we will vote as a whole.
We could follow Alexis
and eliminate Jeremiah.
Or we could just
eliminate Alexis.
The others will have to follow us.
Intelligence is
in a great position.
We just have to order.
The brain controlling the body.
We found our zombies, here we go.
Sarah, a torch is waiting for you.
Take it and turn it on.
It's part of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If your fire goes out,
it's the end for you.
Kass, from the outside,
one would assume
that the three ex-Intelligence
are together,
that the three ex-Beauties
and that Sarah would be in the middle.
That's a pretty good guess.
Morgan, the Beauty tribe: united?
Well, Jeremiah and I
had some difficulties.
Yes, I lied to Morgan.
I chose to eliminate Brice.
It drove Morgan and me apart.
I keep my distance,
I give him his space.
Kass, seeing the issues
between Morgan and Jeremiah,
do you feel calmer?
Yes. You would think that
beautiful people lead the good life.
And then we learn that
all is not rosy there.
It gives a little air to Intelligence.
Despite what we've been through,
it's brought us closer.
What they went through
seems to have separated them.
Spencer, is this beneficial
to the three of Intelligence?
Yes I think so.
But we gotta focus
on reducing divisions
and moving forward united.
Sarah, Spencer isn't wrong.
If you want to go all the way,
and you anticipate a merger,
your group must be united.
Because you don't know what
's going on in the other tribe.
You cannot rely
on old relationships.
I think today
I realized that I was alone.
At the test, Tony shouted,
"Top five! Final five!".
I counted five people in front,
and Sarah wasn't there.
They clearly continue without me.
So it's time
I cut ties with them.
Is this a welcome addition, Alexis?
"It's over with the other tribe".
Yes, that sounds positive, in theory.
But it is always possible
that links will be recreated.
We have to think about it.
Especially tonight.
So who's in danger
tonight, Tash?
In your opinion?
Well Jeff,
the Beauties are in danger.
If they're as divided as
they look.
Alexis, tell me about the raid.
The most interesting moment,
that was when they took
Jeremiah aside,
and we don't know what happened.
It is unclear if this was just their way
of giving him a clue about the idol,
or if it was to
make him talk. No idea.
It really stirred things up.
Jeremiah, what's your version?
They gave me
a clue about an idol.
And that made me a big target.
"They gave him a clue,
they took him aside
to talk to him".
But I see clearly in their game.
And I hope they believe me.
Alexis, as Jeremiah spoke,
you seemed to be wondering
if you trusted him.
It's a matter
of trust, isn't it?
Completely.
Tonight, trust is central.
I don't know if he understood
what happened.
He thinks they were aiming for him.
But that was not their goal.
Jeff? I think that at the merger,
Jeremiah or Alexis
could join the other side.
Tasha, you bend over,
you feast.
That's very telling, Jeff.
Both Jeremiah and Alexis
could betray.
And as soon as you believe
one is the best option,
the second makes you doubt it.
Sarah, you're in the middle.
What do you think of all this?
Anything that takes
the target away from me is fine with me.
I'm all for this tribe.
But there's a person here
who will join the other side.
Alexis, you nod.
Yes I agree.
We three are the only ones
with opposite ties.
But only two
have always kept their word.
- You mean, Sarah and you?
- Yes.
Spencer, how
important is this vote?
If we make
the wrong decision,
we will occupy the 11th,
10th, 9th, 8th and 7th places.
It's incredibly important.
This is probably our
most important decision to date.
It's time to vote.
Kass, it's up to you.
A lie is enough
to lose my confidence.
And you've lied a hundred times.
It is you who will betray.
I don't doubt for a moment
that you will betray. You must leave.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote.
Alexis.
Two Alexis votes, one Jeremiah vote.
Three Alexis votes, one Jeremiah vote.
Sixth person eliminated
from Survivor Cagayan.
That's four, that's enough.
Alexis, bring me your torch.
Alexis, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Two things are clear
after this vote.
It was a big vote.
And you were united in
your decision to eliminate Alexis.
The question that remains unanswered:
how strong is
this unit?
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
- A rowboat?
- Something's going on.
A merger causes two alliances
to compete for power.
When these five are here,
it will be them against us.
But one person
holds all the cards.
There are five welders,
five other welders, and me.
I will decide the fate of the game.
I came wanting
to go all the way.
I am an unconditional fan.
I'm heartbroken that I have
n't even reached fusion,
for not even going that far.
I really thought I was doing better.
I'm really disappointed.