translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
18 new castaways
were divided into 3 tribes:
Muscle, Intelligence and Beauty.
And in eight days, things
were anything but predictable.
In the Muscle tribe,
Tony, who played alone...
I am alone.
It's me, myself,
my idol, and me again.
We are four.
...formed several alliances.
I am with you.
You only have me, and vice versa.
Even lying to a
police colleague to achieve his ends.
Cliff and Lindsey want to eliminate you.
It was a lie
to lure him to my side.
The Intelligence tribe
was a disaster.
On what criteria were
the Intelligents chosen?
I would like to see this data.
And for the Beauty tribe,
nothing could go wrong.
But in the immunity test,
everything changed.
The Beauty Tribe is falling apart!
For the first time,
Intelligence did not lose.
The Intelligence tribe gains immunity!
And Beauty lost
her first immunity test.
Approaching the board,
Jeremiah was caught
between two alliances.
Alexis, Jefra and LJ,
and Brice and Morgan.
I am stuck.
At the tribal council,
he rallied the majority...
Third person eliminated
from Survivor Cagayan.
...eliminating Brice, and leaving
Morgan alone, in bad shape.
There are fifteen left,
who will be eliminated tonight?
Let's try not to do that again.
It cost me a lot.
There, I am
emotionally paralyzed.
The counseling did
not go as planned.
I am furious and frustrated.
Jeremiah is a little coward,
he chickened out.
He came to us,
then he changed sides.
It is very likely
that I will leave next,
unless I manage to save myself.
Jeremiah, why
did you change your mind?
You and Brice approached me
with this idea.
And suddenly, you vote for Brice.
I am confused.
I say. It's that...
My first alliance was
with LJ, Alexis and Jefra.
I gave them
my word, and I thought
that was
the best way for me.
He is incredibly good,
socially.
- Brice or LJ?
- Brian. It is good.
It scared me.
Morgan confronted me
in front of everyone.
She asked me why
I changed my mind,
in front of everybody.
Well, no problem.
It's Survivor.
It was a big decision
for me tonight.
It was trying. We'll see
if it was a stupid move.
Alexis, sorry
to have voted for you, but...
I do not know.
Four days ago, Jeremiah launched
this witch hunt against LJ.
He came to see us,
Brice and me, and told us
that LJ had to go out,
that he was his main opponent.
All that stuff he's willing
to sacrifice his partner
because we need
LJ in the trials.
- I'm sorry, Alexis.
- So I was an easy target.
I'm skeptical
of what Morgan says,
that it was Jeremiah
who planned to eliminate me.
But the way she says it,
it seems vaguely plausible.
Thanks for your honesty.
So I have to keep an eye on it.
Jeremiah? I do not know.
I think he stuck
a big target in his back.
We have mail.
"Can you see yourself in chief?
Can you see your tribe falling?
Can you see protein
at the end of the win?
When you ca
n't see anything at all."
This is the game
blindfolded and the guide.
Apparently,
it's just a reward.
Yes, probably.
It is an important test.
We want to consolidate our victory.
We want to show that our tribe
is capable of playing.
- Coaching.
- We can do it.
Let's visualize this.
Spencer, right.
Honestly, I was thinking
of leaving last time.
Just like the time before.
Because I threw away the rice.
It is because of me that we are hungry.
I'Tia, left.
I want to help them
with food,
because I put us
in this situation.
I'm going to rock
in this ordeal.
J'Tia, a little to the left.
Over here, everyone!
discover the new Beauty tribe.
Brice was eliminated from the council.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today,
one person will be your guide.
The rest of the tribe
will be blindfolded.
Only by voice, the guide
will lead a pair of team members
to collect five items.
As soon as you have one,
you have to bring it back
and hoist it up to the guide.
Once all five items have been collected,
the guide will send you to
get a flag.
The first two tribes
to bring back their flag
to their guide
earn a reward.
Normally, I would ask
you if you want to know what is at stake,
but I believe you hear it.
- Want to see what's at stake?
- Yes!
For the first tribe:
three laying hens and a rooster.
For the second tribe:
A dozen eggs.
Not as good, but not bad.
Anything.
Muscle, two people
will not participate.
Keep in mind
that the same people
cannot stay away
two races in a row.
Woo and Sarah will not participate.
- Beauty, you have one more member.
- I'm not participating.
Morgan is not participating
for the Beauty Tribe.
One minute to organize yourself,
and we'll begin.
Alright, here we go.
For the reward,
Survivors, ready?
Left, left!
Straight ahead, five steps!
Communication is the key.
Kass, you got it!
Kass and Spencer have an item
for the Intelligence tribe.
LJ and Jefra have an item
for the Beauty Tribe.
A bit more! Its good!
Once back, you have
to put it on the platform
and hoist it.
It takes a lot of teamwork
and coordination.
Shoot, shoot!
And then it falls.
Carry on!
Beauty is the first tribe
to bring back an object
- and to hoist it to its guide.
- Carry on!
Cliff sends his tribe
to the farthest place
to start with the hardest.
Intelligence is always
on its first object.
They are close.
Tasha has it!
Each tribe must
collect five items,
no longer their flag.
Beauty has its second object.
Tony and Lindsey bring back
the first object for Muscle.
Put it there, drop it.
Splendid.
LJ, left.
The only place
we would like to avoid,
and LJ got it.
- That's it?
- Yes!
The Intelligence tribe
has its second object.
Now we have to come back.
- Muscle has its first object.
- Let's go!
Beauty now has
its second object, that's it.
While Muscle
goes to get his second object.
Lindsey takes a punch in the stomach.
LJ and Jefra return
with their third item.
Great teamwork
from the Beauty tribe.
- PULL! Stop!
- Intelligence has its second object.
They can leave.
Tony and Lindsey have
the second object for Muscle,
but they have to bring it back.
Left, Spencer, left!
- How are you?
- Stop, let them pass!
- I got it!
- Beauty is in the lead.
They have their third object.
Come on, let's go, over here!
Straight!
You will bump into yourself!
Sorry.
LJ starts to get frustrated.
- To the left!
- Right, right, LJ!
Okay, forward!
Spencer and Kass return
with their third item.
Spencer takes a bad hit
in the same spot as LJ.
- I got it.
- Yeah!
Muscle has its second object.
They're going to get the third one.
Straight on, LJ, straight on!
Okay, stop, LJ!
To your right, LJ!
Intelligence hoists
its third object.
I got it, let go!
Three for Intelligence,
three for Beauty, two for Muscle.
Beauty returns
with its fourth object.
This ordeal will leave
its mark, that's for sure.
-LJ!
- Come on, stay with me!
Muscle returns
with its third item.
Go on! Turn around! Picked up!
Intelligence returns
with a fourth object.
Beauty hoists her fourth object.
- I got it!
- Alexis has it!
Beauty takes the lead.
- I got it!
- Muscle has its third object.
Straight! Hurry up!
Intelligence hoists its fourth object.
I got it!
Equality.
Intelligence and Beauty
have four, Muscle have three.
Right, right!
- I can not hear you.
- Straight!
- Yeah, let's go!
- Beauty has its fifth object.
- All right, LJ.
- Intelligence has its fifth object.
- Straight!
- It was neck and neck the whole time.
Come on, hurry up!
Tony has the fourth item for Muscle.
Got it, here we go, Linds.
Beauty returns
with its fifth object.
- That's perfect.
- Run, run!
Spencer and Kass return
with their fifth object.
Kass crashes into a barrel.
It will leave a mark.
- Ready? PULL!
- Beauty and Intelligence neck and neck.
Carry on! Come on, Spencer!
- Intelligence loses its object.
- Get her back down!
- Got it, go ahead!
- Beauty takes the lead.
All they need now is
their tribe's flag.
Intelligence has just
made a big mistake.
Yeah, spear, Ton!
Come on, we're late,
we have to put the package!
Intelligence tries again
to hoist this fifth object.
Intelligence leaves to seek its flag.
Muscle has its fourth object.
He is upstairs.
Beauty leads.
Intelligence is behind.
Muscle is losing ground.
Come on, get excited!
Straight!
LJ and Jefra have their flag,
they're coming back.
Muscle returns with its fifth
object. Hurry up!
LJ and Jefra are close
to the goal and the victory.
Spencer, flag, flag!
- U-turn!
- Lord!
Beauty is back with her flag,
they just have to hoist it.
Kass and Spencer
have their flag, they're coming back.
Two tribes earn a reward.
- Beauty is near.
- ...Two three...
Closer and closer.
Alexis has the flag!
Beauty wins the reward!
Three laying hens and a rooster!
Two, one, two!
Let's go!
Cliff has the fifth item
for the Muscle Tribe.
They can go back there.
Muscle goes to get his flag.
You must run!
Intelligence already has its own,
but they struggled
to hoist their items.
Straight, straight!
Intelligence,
back with its flag.
Tony and Lindsey
look for their flag.
Can they reach it in time
and come back? That's the question.
Pull it a little bit, that's it.
- Its good?
- Yes.
This ordeal escapes them.
Tony waves his arms frantically.
The Intelligence flag
is on the platform.
- Once again, it falls!
- He fell, J'Tia!
Intelligence loses its means
at the stage of the platform.
Tony and Lindsey have the
Muscle Tribe flag.
You are still in the race!
- Come on, let's hurry!
- Come on!
To the right!
Put it on the right.
Here it is, like this.
No, further forward! Nope!
I Tia try to place it
on the platform,
while Tony and Lindsey
run back.
We have real competition!
Oh, Lindsey takes another hit!
- She falls!
- Hurry up!
Get your hand back!
Your hand, not the flag!
- A little to the left.
- Go on!
Go on!
J'Tia panic.
Intelligence fails
to put it on the platform.
It will be an incredible comeback,
and a huge setback for Intelligence.
Go on!
Rise, rise!
Unbelievable! Muscle placed him
on the platform!
- OK.
- Let's go!
The Muscle Tribe hoists their flag.
A huge comeback!
Muscle finishes second, unheard of!
Intelligence loses the test,
victory was at hand.
Never
give up in this game!
It was hard.
No big deal, we did a good job.
Beauty, very good communication,
huge effort, big reward.
Three laying hens and a rooster.
Come get your reward,
get your stuff,
return to camp and enjoy.
Muscle, good effort to go up.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Enjoy your eggs.
Intelligence,
a huge wasted opportunity.
Spencer, you threw away
your bandana in disgust.
It's frustrating. We were so close.
We thought we would win,
so the disappointment is huge.
Intelligence,
I have nothing for you.
Grab your things
and head back to camp.
This reward event
was a lot of fun.
She kind of gathered the group together,
she reminded us that we are
all here to win, to fight,
and we can win.
It's a beautiful day.
There's food left
for them in there.
But we could
give them a little more.
- Oh, a message!
- Read the message!
"Walk along the rocks.
It's easier at low tide.
Spend some time near the reef,
and you could be protected tonight.
Attached to solid is
the idol you seek,
well hidden, but not too deep.
You'll have to get wet."
That is why? The hidden idol?
Oh yeah.
Jeremiah finds
the clue for the idol in the bag.
Alas, everyone is there.
The clue was so precise.
Thank God I have it, because it
would have been found today.
It would have been a collective idol,
and therefore a huge problem.
I had never been so
close to a live chicken.
So the rooster has
to climb on one of the hens
- to make eggs?
- I wondered.
- Nope.
- Nope?
Are the eggs still coming out?
- Yes.
- To make chicks.
- So what is the rooster for?
There was a chicken and egg debate .
But I think
they pretend to know.
So they are, what, asexual?
What makes them
lay eggs?
They need something, like...
A heat lamp.
No one knows how
chickens are born.
I don't know, I...
I find it hard to believe that people
can say such things.
You don't have any eggs, do you?
Ah, so a guy has to come and...
We have the
Beauty tribe stereotype.
It's really unfortunate.
I don't think that's it.
I don't know.
I just know they
taste really good.
We all know
the egg was there before,
because the dinosaurs
laid them.
And they were there
before the chickens, so...
You'll be delicious, I'm sorry.
Do you do it or do you want
me to?
- You can do it?
- I will do it.
- I leave you.
- Just in case.
It's a little hard,
because after the advice,
I gotta work
my southern charm,
stay in their good graces,
I try to take the lead
and do as much as possible.
- Oh Lord.
- Lord.
Oh my God.
It's a head, is it detached?
- Yes.
- I know how to work.
He ripped it off.
Chickens don't need
brains to function?
It will continue to move.
It was disgusting.
Jeremiah, looks
like you've done this before.
I hope I scored
some points today.
I grew up in the countryside,
but I don't know anything about chickens.
I'm a model, you know?
Jeremiah killed the chicken,
and that's cool.
I will be able to eat it,
I appreciate it, I will say thank you.
It's the best idea
since we've been here.
But in the end, I do
n't like Jeremiah at all.
He is dumb as his feet.
And he's a big liar.
I don't understand why
he is in this tribe.
He is not handsome enough
for the tribe of the handsomest.
We're going to have to stick together.
Of course we're going to have
to stick together.
Sooner or later there will be...
A surprise elimination.
Don't take this the wrong way, but you
guys are very emotional.
- Do you want me to do more?
- Nope.
- Oh, let's go.
- No, I do not want.
Cliff and Lindsey are very close.
They want to eliminate me.
Tony heard them and told me.
If you come after me,
I'll come after you, only worse.
I want Cliff gone.
I like Cliff, but
he doesn't need the money.
- We do.
- Yeah.
What if we lose...
The next... Cliff?
- Possible.
- Good.
It's a big
necessary move in this game.
We are young.
You know what I mean?
- It's our turn to shine.
- I agree.
Woo would turn on Cliff,
that surprised me.
He has a nonchalant attitude.
Me too.
Woo really wants to win.
It is an impression,
a feeling.
But I believe we are allies.
I like the idea
that our chances of winning
- are much more important.
- Than hers.
- He's already rich.
- I say.
I really admire Cliff,
he's a basketball superstar.
I have idealized him for a long time.
But it would be nice
if one of us,
other than Cliff, become a millionaire.
When we say his name,
it means it's time.
High five. OK?
I try to relate to the majority.
When the opportunity arises,
I have to seize it.
In the end, I want us...
Yeah, I agree.
We agree.
We agree, Tony.
Just tell me
what's going on, okay?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
I saw Woo and Sarah whisper.
I asked what was going on.
I walked up, and they were...
Like a deer in the headlights,
as soon as I approached.
I took Sarah aside
to ask her what was going on.
Woo is with us.
- You are sure of it?
- Positively.
A few days ago
I lied to Sarah,
telling him that Cliff
and Lindsey wanted to eliminate him.
I believe that from there,
I changed the game
by luring him to my side.
I believe that now
she is my ally.
Tell me the truth,
I trust you,
I believe in your word.
You tell me to trust
Woo, that's alright,
but I don't trust him.
For Sarah, Woo is on her side,
and therefore it is also mine.
So we have
a covenant of four now,
against Cliff and Lindsey.
Swear on your badge
not to betray me.
On everything I love,
I will not betray you.
She made me swear on my badge.
It doesn't mean anything to me.
I'm here to
lie, cheat and steal.
I'm here to destroy
other people's dreams for my own.
I am here for this.
I will do what it takes.
It's that simple.
Two cops in the final.
We have never seen that.
A little mail.
Let's see.
“Castaway on an island
is always swim or sink.
You will sink today
if you don't score a basket.
The tribal council
could be dismal."
Score a basket, man,
score a basket.
It's you, Cliff.
We have an
immunity test today.
And it could be basketball.
I'm sure everyone
expects me to score,
because I played basketball.
It looks fun.
I spent 18 years in the NBA.
I was in the ten best
players of all time.
I played more games
than Michael Jordan,
So hopefully
it will be a walk.
Here's the thing, Trish.
Come on, I listen to you.
First, Lindsey will not participate.
So you, me and Woo
can easily lose on purpose.
I know we said
we'd never lose on purpose,
because it doesn't work.
However,
we cannot risk
that Cliff is still there
during the merge.
I've never done anything like that,
it's a funny feeling.
But I can do it,
trust me.
Sounds stupid.
Why renounce the majority?
But he's not in
our majority, that's why.
It's Lindsey and him.
I was told that
Cliff wanted to eliminate me.
So I'm doomed
if Cliff's still here.
And if it shows that we lost
on purpose, it doesn't matter. He will leave.
The problem is convincing Woo.
Let's lose on purpose and eliminate it.
Trish is in.
But we have the majority.
What if we merge?
Losing on purpose is not smart.
Some of them
may want to do it,
but Cliff and I
are very close.
And I can imagine it.
Putting baskets.
Look at this throw!
It's undeniable.
With my buddy Cliff!
But my allies
think differently.
So what to do?
Damn it!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
Yeah.
First, approach
the idols and throw them at me.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will dive
to release a buoy.
When you have it, come back,
and the next one goes.
When you have all five buoys,
you will throw them into a basket.
The first two tribes
to achieve this
gain immunity,
are protected from voting.
The losers will go to the council,
where a fourth person will be eliminated.
Muscle, you're two more.
Who will not participate?
Remember
it can't be
the same people
two events in a row.
Tony and Lindsey will not participate.
Beauty, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
- Moi.
- Alexis.
Alexis will not participate.
The others, you have
one minute to organize yourselves
and we start.
For immunity,
Survivors, ready?
J'Tia!
The first buoy is
one meter deep.
It will be the easiest.
LJ goes up first
for the Beauty tribe.
Woo reassembled for the Muscle Tribe.
J'Tia is still on it.
She can not.
Jefra is in the water
for the Beauty tribe.
Sarah is in the water
for the Muscle Tribe.
Jefra has the second buoy
of the Beauty tribe.
At only one meter deep,
J'Tia does not succeed.
She comes back,
wasting them a ton of time.
Sarah is still at work.
Now it's Tasha's turn.
She will try to bring back
the buoy that J'Tia left.
Once again, Intelligence
is quickly left behind.
Sarah finally has her buoy
for the Muscle tribe.
It took him a long time.
She has it, Tasha comes back.
Morgan has the third buoy
of the Beauty tribe.
Trish is in the water
for the Muscle Tribe.
Tasha brought back the first
intelligence tribe buoy.
Now it's Trish
who's having trouble.
Jeremiah fetches the
Beauty Tribe's fourth buoy.
Kass returns empty-handed.
The second member of Intelligence
who returns empty-handed.
Spencer will try
to shake things up.
Jeremiah returns with the fourth
buoy of the Beauty tribe.
Trish returns empty-handed
for the Muscle Tribe.
Giving Intelligence
a chance to return.
Spencer brings back the second
intelligence tribe buoy.
LJ goes to look for the fifth
and last buoy.
Tasha goes to get
the third buoy.
Cliff fetches the
Muscle Tribe's third buoy.
Tasha comes up empty-handed.
LJ goes down to 4 meters 50
and quickly returns with
the fifth and last buoy.
Go into the water,
start casting.
The Beauty tribe dominates.
The Intelligence tribe is
still on its third buoy.
Cliff has the third buoy.
Spencer has the third buoy.
They are neck and neck.
It's Jeremiah and Morgan shooting.
Jeremiah scores a first point.
Spencer returns to the water
for Intelligence.
Jeremiah scores a second point
for the Beauty tribe.
Woo must descend to 3.50 meters
for the fourth buoy.
Spencer, back again
with another buoy.
Spencer single-handedly keeps
his team in the running.
Jeremiah scores a third point
for the Beauty Tribe.
Woo comes back with
the fourth buoy for Muscle.
4.50 meters, and Spencer brings
in the fifth and last buoy.
Jeremiah scores a fourth point.
Like at the carnival.
And that's it!
The Beauty Tribe wins immunity!
Protected from the tribal council!
We need another tribe.
Spencer returns with the fifth
buoy for Intelligence.
He's worn out.
Intelligence can start shooting.
Woo will have to descend to 4.50 meters
to free the last buoy.
Spencer is going to shoot for Intelligence.
Intelligence has
another problem now.
Neither of the two women in the water
can't get
the ball back to Spencer.
Woo is still underwater
for Muscle.
Can he bring back a buoy?
Woo has the fifth buoy
for Muscle.
You must bring her back.
Spencer scores a first point
for Intelligence.
Against all expectations,
they remain in the race.
There you go, Muscle, you've got all five.
You can start shooting.
Spencer scores a second
point for Intelligence.
It's a duel at the top
between Spencer and Cliff.
Intelligence has two points,
Muscle must place the five buoys.
Spencer's enters and exits.
Cliff scores a first
point for Muscle.
Good job, good job!
You have to hurry
if you want to bounce back.
J'Tia loses the buoy for Intelligence.
You need to get it back fast
to be able to shoot.
Cliff scores a second
point for Muscle.
Tied, 2-2.
Cliff scores a third
point for Muscle.
Spencer is still waiting for
the ball, frustrated.
Make good passes,
or you're wasting time.
Cliff scores a fourth point.
More than one for Muscle,
is it this one?
Spencer scores a third
point for Intelligence.
There are 4 to 3.
Cliff enters and exits.
Spencer shoots the fourth.
She goes in and out.
That's it, Cliff scores
the fifth point for Muscle!
Muscle gains immunity!
Once again sending
Intelligence to the council.
Here, Alexis.
Immunity for the Beauty Tribe.
No Tribal Council
for the Muscle Tribe.
Intelligence, good effort,
but just insufficient.
Once again, advice.
One of you will be
the fourth eliminated from this game.
See you tonight at the council.
We tried so hard
to lose this event.
Seriously, Intelligence,
I tried to help you!
But this team sucks.
They deserve
to lose after that.
That's all I can say.
- Spencer, you rocked.
- It's hard.
- You ripped.
- It's my fault.
No, it was a collective effort.
I don't blame
anyone in particular.
I'm just disappointed that we lost.
I feel a little scammed
to have to go to the council,
while I do
very well in the trials.
It's my team
that doesn't do it at all.
- Spencer, you nailed it.
- Yeah, you did.
- It was so tight...
- Really tight.
The worst thing about this tribe
is that the girls have managed
to take a dominant position.
The problem is that by doing that,
they put the tribe down.
J'Tia keeps screwing up
in the trials.
It's beyond frustrating.
History does not preach
in my favor.
I am an asset in the trials.
- You agree?
- Yes.
I think J'Tia
is quite the opposite.
If we keep losing
and we're decimated,
- we're all in trouble.
- Exactly.
The best thing for the tribe
is to keep me.
I don't know if they
comfort me before they take me out,
or if they are really trying to reinstate me.
Spencer can't
be trusted.
Is there any logic
in eliminating Spencer?
At this point, no.
If I could I would.
- But J'Tia can't do anything.
- Light.
We can't win with her.
Yes, we will be eliminated one by one
if we don't have
the best possible tribe.
Namely you, Spencer and me.
I'm happy with our decision,
eliminating J'Tia makes sense.
If we have another event,
we will have a tough guy with us.
Rather than someone
known to have a propensity for failure.
I don't want to tell him
he's safe.
Absolutely not.
I want us to play
it like it's him.
And that J'Tia feels perfectly
safe, to avoid any new...
I'm still mad about the rice.
- Let's go.
- It's hard, I like Spencer.
- Light.
- Like us.
- If we keep it,
and there's a merge
or something,
he will go with the men.
The important thing is trust.
At some point in the game, you have
to be able to trust someone.
And I don't
trust Spencer.
I have for me to be loyal.
But let's be honest. On the 6th day,
I threw the rice on the fire.
Since then, I cling
by the nails,
like the cat on the poster.
"Hold on!"
It's me.
My best bet
is that my wedding ring holds.
If tomorrow the tribes are mixed,
I trust you more than...
You have done a lot for me.
Whatever happens, if we're mixed up,
I'm with you.
- Yes.
- I believe you.
I believe you more than Spencer.
Initially, I was thinking
of voting for J'Tia,
but I believe J'Tia loyal.
Thank you, ladies.
And you never know, Jeff might
have a surprise in store for us.
In a game where you
need someone loyal.
It is to be taken into account.
Are we in this game
to win races?
Or to go as far as
possible with loyal people?
If we're mixed up, I guarantee you
we can count on J'Tia.
The interesting with Tasha,
it is like a pendulum,
here one moment, there the next.
It will change maybe
five more times before the council.
I want her to leave.
But then
I think for a moment:
for the long term, is this
the wisest thing to do?
You make sense,
I wanted to talk to you about it.
' Cause I might
miss the mark, Kass.
Either way, it's a risk.
Tasha can't stop thinking about it.
I say:
make a decision and let it flow!
But this is my life.
I always have to decide
for others and live with them.
So we're gonna
kick out J'Tia or Spencer.
I can live
with both decisions.
For me, it's a gamble
either way,
because I can't predict
what will happen tomorrow.
J'Tia, what place
do you occupy in this group,
in terms of responsibility
for the defeats?
Honestly, today
in the water I did my best.
It's a
strange position for me.
Generally, in situations
of great stress, I excel.
I don't think I have
any physical shortcomings.
But swimming is not my thing.
Tasha, does that sound right to you,
that J'Tia was weak
only once, namely today?
No, J'Tia was weak in
most events, Jeff.
In the tests, we must
find a role for him
which is as small as possible.
J'Tia, how does it feel
to hear someone say
that if he voted for the
weak link, it would be you?
She says I'm
the weakest in trials,
not that I'm the weak link.
Big difference.
Survivor isn't just about
being stronger, it's also about being smarter.
You have to take that into account.
But you forget one aspect,
which is that you have to
hold out long enough
to outlast the others.
And at this rate, none of you
will be there in the end.
That's the real dilemma,
isn't it, Tasha?
This is the decision to be made.
Do we keep the strongest
to the trials, Spencer?
Him who kicked me out of the alliance
with him and Garrett.
Or do we choose
the one who has proven her loyalty?
Kass, what happens
when you factor in
that J'Tia threw
95% of your rice on the fire?
I view this incident
as an emotional response,
not as a sign of disloyalty.
It's a hothead.
But I understand it,
I was too.
Doesn't mean
I'm not loyal,
just that I made
bad decisions.
The problem is that these decisions
can cost you a million.
Yes, tonight, I could make
a very bad decision.
I feel the weight of it.
Spencer, how
do you feel about all of this?
I believe the rice
does not plead for it.
Maybe you give
signs of loyalty,
but being unpredictable is
as dangerous as being disloyal.
I won't make
that kind of stupid mistake.
And I will move forward with this group.
You've said that before, so...
Yes, and I think...
I can't help it, I was the jerk
on the wrong side of the vote the other time.
J'Tia and Spencer, are you aware
that while you're chatting,
Kass and Tasha talk to each other?
I hear them whisper in front of me.
I know what we talked about
before coming.
I hope the alliance will hold.
Spencer, they...
Nod to each other.
That's crazy. As a
viewer, I would love that,
but here, now,
it's rather creepy.
Kass, you seem to be enjoying this.
If I was in front of my TV,
"Don't do anything stupid, Tash!"
"Don't do anything stupid, Kass!"
But what is stupid?
- That's the question.
- That's the question now.
And you, Spencer?
What do you feel?
Are you a big fan of the show?
and you haven't really had
a chance to actually play.
It's infuriating.
And at this point, I'm
ready to do anything to avoid it.
Tash doesn't even listen to you.
She looks at Kass
and they seek the decision.
It is decided at this moment.
I mean I'm
loyal to you two.
I want to help you
win events.
All I ask
is an opportunity.
Well, it's time to vote.
Kass, it's up to you.
I've never been
so nervous in my life.
I know it's you or me.
So there is nothing to think about.
I've been on probation since
I threw the rice away.
I hope it's you and not me.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote.
J'Tia.
I Tia.
Two J'Tia votes, one Spencer vote.
One vote remains.
Fourth person eliminated
from Survivor Cagayan.
J'Tia.
Bring me your torch.
Good luck to you.
- Thanks.
J'Tia, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
I will prove
to you that you have done well.
I say.
- I am with you 100%.
- I say.
With all the ups and downs
of this tribe,
the only constant is
that you remain unpredictable.
Let's hope this new
configuration brings you stability,
because you need it.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
It was really intense.
The Intelligence tribe
is on the verge of extinction.
Our way of playing is ridiculous.
We are not "Intelligence",
we are "Imbecility".
But a turnaround
revives the game.
Throw away your bandanas.
Intelligence, Muscle
and Beauty no longer exist.
I'm not surprised
they eliminated me.
I threw away all the rice
and was weak in the trials.
So yes, these are good
reasons to eliminate me.
What to say?
I am shared.
I wish them good luck,
and at the same time I hope
they will starve.
But that's life.
You live, you learn
from your mistakes, you grow.
I'll just grow
outside of the game.