>> PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR.
>> THERE ARE TWO OPTIONS
>>BLACK GETS YOU THE ADVANTAGE
>> FOR 30 DAYS SPENCER AND
TONY HAVE BEEN ON OPPOSITE
PATHS.
>> BOTH PUT YOUR PALMS OUT.
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING HAS GONE
RIGHT FOR TONY.
HE'S BEEN AT THE TOP OF THE
MAJORITY ALLIANCE AND HAS
MULTIPLE IDOLS.
>> YOU HAVE BEEN FINDING THE
ONE WITH DIFFERENT POWERS.
>> I HAVE TWO IDOLS IN MY
POSSESSION.
>> FOR SPENCER.
>> BLACK IS THE ADVANTAGE
WITNESS'S BEEN A DIFFERENT
STORY.
HIS LIFE IN THE GAME HAS
BEEN A CONSTANT STRUGGLE.
>> YOU HAVE AS MANY CLUES AS
YOU WANT,.
>> HE WASTED HIS ONLY IDOL.
>> JEREMIAH.
>> AND HIS ALLIES HAVE BEEN
PICKED OFF ONE BY ONE.
>> SEE YOU.
>> BUT THINGS STARTED TO
TURN AROUND.
>> SPENCER HAS IT.
>> HE WON IMMUNITY.
THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE WAS
TURNING ON EACH OTHER.
>> YOU WRITE MY NAME DOWN
AND YOU'RE GOING HOME.
>> HE EVEN MADE A FINAL
THREE PACT WITH KASS AND
WOO.
>> AND THEY TARGETED TONY.
BUT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL IT
FELL APART ONCE AGAIN.
KASS REALIZED TONY HAD
ENEMIES.
>> TONY PUT MOST OF THOSE
PEOPLE OVER THERE BUT NO ONE
WANTS TO SEE IT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: AND SHE DECIDED TO
KEEP HIM.
>> SPENCER COULD ONLY WATCH
AS THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE
TOOK OUT HIS ONLY ALLY.
>> TASHA, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT.
>> PART TWO?
SO WHAT WAS THE POINT OF THE
WHOLE WHOLE SHENANIGAN?
JUST FOR FUN OR WHAT?
>> WE MADE A FINAL THREE
DEAL, SO WHAT WAS THE POINT
OF THAT DOING THAT IF YOU
DIDN'T MEAN IT.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GUYS ARE
PROPOSING BUT I ALREADY HAVE
A FINAL THREE.
>> AT TRIBE AT COUNCIL KASS
AND WOO VOTED FOR TASHA SO
IT TURNS OUT THE DEAL THAT
WE HAD WAS A LIE.
SO I LEFT TRIBAL KIND OF
CONFUSED.
>> YOU COULD HAVE JUST TOLD
ME YOU WERE VOTING TASHA OUT
AND THERE'S NOTHING I COULD
HAVE DONE ABOUT IT.
WHY BOTHER WITH THE WHOLE
CHARADE.
>> WHY DOES ANYONE LIE IN
THIS GAME, IT'S PART OF THE
GAME.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY I
REALIZED THAT TONY HAS BEEN
A JERK TO PRETTY MUCH
EVERYONE AT SOME POINT IF
THE GAME.
MAYBE I WOULD RATHER GO TO
THE END WITH TONY WHO HAS
BURNED SO MANY BRIDGES AND
JUST BEEN SO OBNOXIOUS THAT
NOBODY WANTS HIM TO WIN.
>> I GUESS THE BOTTOM LINE
IS, SPINESER, THEY WERE
TOYING WITH YOU.
>> RIGHT, THEY WERE TOIING
WITH ME, JUST FOR FUN.
>> THAT'S LOILTS, MY FRIEND.
>> THEY ARE LOYAL.
>> AS LONG AS THEY DON'T
STAB ME IN THE BACK I WILL
NEVER STAB THEM IN THE BACK.
>> I AM PLAYING AGAINST TONY
WHO HAS PLAYED ALL THESE
PEOPLE LIKE A FIDDLE AND
THREE FOOLISH PLAYERS WHO
DON'T THINK FOR THEMSELVES
AND I'M ALMOST DEFINITELY
NEXT TO GO.
BUT IF I HAVE ANY HOPE IN
THE GAME, IT'S THE FACT THAT
I'M PLAYING WITH PEOPLE WHO
UNDERSTAND IT SO LITTLE.
>> SO YEAH THIS IS IT, MAN,
THE FINAL STRETCH, MY
FRIEND.
>> I'M GOING INTO THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE FEELING
SUPERCONFIDENT I'M GOING TO
WIN.
>> ME TOO, MAN.
>> AND I I'M GOING OUT THERE
AND I'M GOING TO TRY TO WIN
JUST SO SPENCER DOESN'T WIN.
>> RIGHT.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
FINAL THREE.
YOU KNOW IF KASS WENT TO THE
END SHE AIN'T GET NOTHING
VOTES.
SHE WOULD BE PERFECT FOR
FINAL 3.
ME, YOU AND HER SHE GETS NO
VOTES.
>> I DID CONSIDER BLINDSIDING
TONY BUT IT'S A MOVE THAT I
DECIDED NOT TO MAKE BECAUSE
HONESTLY I FEEL LIKE SITTING
NEXT TO TONY AT THE END OF
THE GAME, TOP THREE WOULD BE
A LOVELY THING SINCE WE
STARTED THIS GAME TOGETHER
SO I NEED HIM TO SEE ME AS
SOMEONE THAT WOULDN'T BACK
STAB HIM, SOMEONE WHO WOULD
BE LOYAL TO HIM TO THE END.
SO I DECIDED TO FILL HIM IN
WITH WHAT WENT DOWN WITH THE
REWARDS.
>> SINCE WE WERE GOING TO
VOTE FOR YOU, THAT WAS HIS
GAME PLAN, WHICH KASS WAS IN
ON.
>> WOW, MAN.
>> SHE EVEN TOLD ME HEY, I
THINK WOULD BE BETTER IF WE
WIN TOP THREE BEING ME, KASS
AND SPENCER.
>> TELL ME ABOUT IT.
>> IT WAS GOOD THAT YOU CAME
TO ME BECAUSE THAT JUST
SHOWS ME INTEGRITY, YOUR
LOYALTY.
HE'S BEEN WITH ME SINCE THE
BEGINNING.
HE HAS PROVEN HIS TRUST AND
LOYALTY TO ME THROUGHOUT.
THE KID IS GENUINE AND IT
TEARS ME APART THAT I'M
GOING TO HAVE TO EVENTUALLY
BLINDSIDE HIM.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO TAKE
SOMEONE LIKABLE TO THE END
BECAUSE HE MIGHT HAVE A SHOT
OF GETTING A FEW VOTES, HE
MIGHT GET A LOT OF VOTES.
THAT'S NOT GOOD FOR
BUSINESS.
I'M THINKING ABOUT MY
FAMILY.
MY WIFE TOLD ME TONY, WHEN
YOU GO OUT THERE, DON'T DO
ANYTHING STUPID.
TRY TO WIN THE GAME.
TAKING HIM TO THE END IS
STUPID.
I WILL LISTEN MY WIFE ON
THIS ONE
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO DIVE INTO A PIT OF
MUD AND COVER YOUR BODY WITH
MUD.
YOU'LL THEN RACE BACK AND
SCRAPE THE MUD OFF INTO A
BUCKET.
YOU CANNOT CARRY MUD IN ANY
FASHION.
THE PERSON WITH THE MOST MUD
IN THEIR BUCKET AFTER TEN
MINUTES WINS A REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> AFTER 34 DAYS IN THESE
CONDITIONS NOT ONLY DO YOU
MISS COMFORT FOOD FROM HOME
BUT YOU MISS THE CONVENIENCE
OF HAVING THAT COMFORT FOOD
DELIVERED TO YOUR HOME.
THE WINNER OF TODAY'S
CHALLENGE WILL HAVE PIPING
HOT PIZZA DELIVERED TO YOU
AT CAMP.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SIT
AND EAT.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
DRAW UP YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO, FOR
REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY.
GO!
>> I SEE PEOPLE HOPPING,
SOME SLIDING THROUGH,
DOESN'T MATTER, JUST GET IN
THAT MUD.
>> BIG QUESTION IS WHAT
STRATEGY WILL YOU USE TO GET
THE MUD BACK.
WHATEVER YOU CAN GET TO
STICK TO YOUR BODY WORKS.
>> TONY COMING BACK, TRISH
COMING BACK KASS REALLY
TAKING HER TIME THE GOAL IS
TO GET AS MUCH MUD AS YOU
CAN IN THAT BUCKET.
YOU HAVE 10 MINUTES TO DO
IT.
KEEP IN MIND YOU CAN'T CARRY
MUD T THAT WOULD BE THE EASY
THING TO DO.
SPENCER BACK OUT.
WOO BACK OUT, TRISH COMING
BACK OUT.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT THE
COMBINATION OF GETTING AS
MUCH ON YOUR BODY AS YOU CAN
BUT THEN GETTING WHAT IS ON
YOUR BODY INTO THE BUCKETS.
TONY WITH A LOT OF MUD
COMING OFF THOSE ARMS.
WOO IS USING HIS HAIR TO
TRANSPORT MUD AND IT'S
WORKING.
KASS, FACE FIRST, THAT IS
HOW YOU DO IT AFTER 34 DAYS
ON SURVIVOR.
TONY WITH A LOT OF MUD.
WOO BACK WITH A LOT OF MUD.
SPENCER SCRAPING IT ALL OFF.
EVERYBODY HEADING BACK OUT
FOR MORE MUD.
TWO MINUTES LEFT.
KEEP MOVING.
WOO FLYING THROUGH.
KASS WITH AN AMAZING LIVING
ART SCULPTURE.
ONE MINUTE LEFT IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
ONE MINUTE.
RIGHT NOW IT IS TONY, WOO
AND SPENCER, KASS AND TRISH
FALLING BEHIND.
MAKE YOUR LAST RUN.
LOAD UP.
YOU'VE GOT ONE MORE CHANCE
TO GET IN THAT PIT AND GET
AS MUCH MUD AS YOU CAN.
YOU NEVER GIVE UP IN THIS
GAME.
TONY WITH A LOT OF MUD.
WOO COMING BACK WITH MUD.
SPENCER COMING BACK.
TRISH AND KASS COMING BACK,
THIS IS IT, GOING TO BE YOUR
LAST ROUND, GET AS MUCH AS
YOU CAN OFF YOUR BODY AND
INTO THIS BUCKET.
EVERYBODY COVERED IN MUD.
LAST FIVE SECONDS, FIVE,
FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
EVERYBODY STEP AWAY.
GREAT EFFORT.
>> WOW, NOBODY EVEN CAME
CLOSE.
TONY'S BUCKET LITERALLY
OVERFLOWING WITH MUD.
SO SPENCER S THERE ANY
QUESTION ABOUT THIS
CHALLENGE?
DO WE NEED TO WEIGH THEM.
>> WE AGREE THE BUCK SET
PROOF ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, TONY, GET OVER
HERE SO HERE'S THE DEAL.
PIZZA DELIVERED TO YOU BACK
AT CAMP, HOT, CHEESE, ALL
THE FIXINGS.
BUT EVERYBODY KNOWS PIZZA
DELIVERED TO HOME FOR ONE,
KIND OF PATHETIC.
PIZZA FOR TWO THAT'S A
PARTY.
CHOOSE ONE OF THESE FOUR TO
JOIN YOU THIS AFTERNOON,
WHICH MEANS TWO OF YOU WILL
ENJOY PIZZA, THREE OF YOU
WILL NOT.
ANOREXIA, COME ON OVER.
>> YEAH, PIZZA!
I LOVE YOU!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE PICKING
TRISH BASED SIMPLY ON NEED.
>> OF COURSE, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE IS
WHAT WILL YOU HAPPEN.
TONY, TRISH GO BACK TO CAMP,
PIZZA WILL BE DELIVERED TO
YOU AND YOU TWO ONLY.
WOO, KASS, SPENCER, GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU, GRAB
YOURSELF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP
AND ENJOY THE AFTERNOON.
GET ON OUT OF HERE.
>> I FEEL LIKE-- YOU LOOKS
LIKE-- ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD,
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO WET
MY PANTS.
>> SHE STILL HAS IT.
>> OH MY GOODNESS.
LOOK AT THAT THING.
>> I'M ACTUALLY GLAD TONY
PICKED TRISH FOR THE REWARD
BECAUSE IT JUST SOLIDIFIES
THAT THOSE TWO ARE LOCKED
TOGETHER.
TONY IS THE ALPHA MALE OUT
HERE AND SHE'S THE FEMALE.
THEY ARE LIKE A COUPLE OF
BABOONS.
SURPRISED SHE'S NOT PICKING
CHICKS OFF HIM RIGHT NOW.
THEY ARE ATTACHED AT THE HIP
AND EVERYONE CAN SEE IT.
AND IN MY VIEW NO ONE IN
THIS GAME SHOULD HAVE THAT
MUCH POWER.
THE PIZZA REWARD IS KIND OF
LIKE A METAPHOR FOR WHAT'S
GOING ON IN THE GAME.
TONY IS WINNING.
HE'S TAKING LONG TRISH, AND
NO ONE SEEMS TO BE BOTHERED
BY THAT.
EVERYONE SEEMS TO BE HANDY
TONY THIS GAME MUCH LIKE THE
PIZZA ON A SILVER PLATTER.
>> OH PIE GOODNESS, WOULD
YOU LIKE A NAPKIN.
>> OH MY GOD, TONY, YOU'RE
GOING TO TLOUP, STOP.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE HAPPY, BUT
IT'S NOT WORTH IT TO EAT IT
AND HAVE IT ALL COME BACK.
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
SNORT A PIZZA DOWN LIKE
TONY.
IT STARTED COMING OUT OF HIS
NOSE AND EARS, PINEAPPLE
FLYING EVERY WHERE.
I WAS LIKE WHOA, DUDE, SLOW
DOWN.
>> YOU CAN HAVE THIS ONE
HERE.
>> TONY, YOU ATE FIVE.
>> HE DIDN'T HAVE THE
SPECIAL POWER.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DO, BOTH.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU HAVE
BOTH.
>> -- UH-HUH.
>> BOTH THE IDOLS I HAVE NOW,
EVEN THE IDOL WITH THE
SPECIAL POWERS HAVE TO BE
USED WHEN IT'S DOWN TO FIVE
SURVIVORS LEFT.
>> MY INTENTIONS ARE TO LIE
TO THEM AND ACT LIKE THE
SPECIAL POWER IDOL I'M
ALLOWED TO USE IT WHENS
THERE'S FOUR SURVIVORS LEFT.
IF THEY DO FOR ME MY BLUFF,
I'M GUARANTEED FINAL THREE.
>> SHE IS JUST RECKLESS.
>> NORMALLY I WOULD GET HER
OUT OF HERE.
BUT I CAN'T.
I WANT LETTER TO THE END.
>> THE GAME IS IN MY HANDS.
I HAVE THE POWER RIGHT NOW,
I'M IN THE DRIVER SEAT, I
WANT TO STAY STRONG WITH
TRISH AND KASS BECAUSE THOSE
ARE THE TWO LESS LIKELY TO
WIN OVER ME.
>> I KNOW I HAVE TRISH BUT
KASS AND I HAVE TO SOLIDIFY
SOME TYPE OF PLAN.
>> -- THE HELICOPTER
DELIVERING YOUR PIZZA.
>> YOU WON'T.
>> UNLESS YOU WIN THE
MILLION DOLLARS.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING TODAY,
KASS IF.
>> ALL RIGHT, MAN.
>> AN IMPORTANT DAY FOR ALL
OF US.
BECAUSE IF EXPERIENCE IRWINS
ONE OF US GO.
>> I KNOW.
>> SO I'M GOING GIVE IT MY
ALL.
>> I'M GIVING MY ALL.
>> I WANT TO GO IN WITH YOU
AND IN WITH TRISH.
EVEN THOUGH YOU WENT BEHIND
MY BACK THEY TLID TRIED TO
BLINDSIDE ME.
BUT I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT
RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT TAKING IT PERSONAL.
I WANT TO GO WITH YOU AND I
WANT TO GO WITH TRISH.
>> TONY DECIDED TO CONFRONT
ME AND SAY I HEARD THAT YOU
WERE CONSPIRING AGAINST ME
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
WOO TOLD ME ALL THAT AND I'M
OKAY WITH THAT BUT YOU
SHOULDN'T BE DOING THAT.
IT WAS STUPID OF WOO TO TELL
HIM AND TO TELL ME.
>> I WANT TO YOU FEEL
COMFORTABLE AND 100% AND I'M
WITH YOU.
BECAUSE WE WILL AT THE END.
YOU IT'S 50/50.
MY BABY AND WIFE WE'RE
GOING.
>> TONY PLEDGED ON HIS WIFE
AND BABY THAT IT'S STILL
GOING TO TAKE ME TO THE END.
SOIF'S BEEN FORGIVEN BY THE
MAFIA BOSS BUT IF I'M GOING
TO SIT NEXT TO TONY IN THE
FINAL 3 I NEED TO SHOW
EVERYONE THAT TONY IS A
BULLY, JUST AN EXTREMELY
UNLIKEABLE PERSON.
AND HE WON'T GET ANY VOTES
FROM THE JURY.
SO CHAOS KASS IS BACK.
WOO TOLD ME EVERYTHING I
TOLD YOU.
>> HE TOLD ME ON THE BODE
YESTERDAY, YOU TOLD ME
EVERYTHING.
>> WHAT?
>> WOO SAYS HE DIDN'T TELL
YOU ANYTHING ON THE BOAT
YESTERDAY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHO ARE YOU INVESTIGATING?
>> WHY CAN'T I INVESTIGATE.
>> YEAH, ME AND YOU WERE
TALKING AND HE TOLD ME
EVERYTHING HE TOLD ME.
I TOLD YOU SOMETHING IN
SECRECY AND YOU COME HERE
AND BLOW IT OUT.
>> YOU WERE INTERROGATING
ME.
>> INTERROGATING YOU?
I TOLD YOU A FACT.
YOU SAY YOU WENT BEHIND MY
BACK, I DID MAKE THAT UP OUT
OF THE BLUE OR WAS THAT A
FACT.
SHE'S AMAZING.
>> I'M ALLOWED TO CONFRONT
PEOPLE TOO.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> HE SHOOK MY HAND AND
SWORE ON HIS WIFE AND BABY
THAT WE HAVE A FINAL 3.
>> IF PEOPLE TELL SECRETS
AND IT'S PEOPLE LIKE YOU
THAT GO IN AND BLOW THINGS
UP.
>> I TOLD WOO THAT TONY
SWORE ON HIS BABY AND WIFE
ELSE THAT'S TAKING ME TO THE
FINAL 3 BECAUSE AT THIS
POINT YOU WANT AS MUCH
PARANOIAS YOU CAN STIR UP
ESPECIALLY AMONG TIGHT TIGHT
PEOPLE SO HE JUST SCREWED
HIMSELF BECAUSE NOW PERHAPS
WOO DOESN'T TRUST HIM.
>> SO.
>> PLEASE DON'T TALK TO ME.
>> EVERYBODY IS A LAWED TO
TALK TO TONY BUT NOBODY IS
ALLOWED TO TALK TO EACH
OTHER.
>> THAT IS HOW INTELLIGENT
YOU ARE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
TALKING TO PEOPLE AND REVEALING
SECRETS IS A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT ANIMAL.
WHEN I TOLD YOU THAT, YOU
WERE WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO
TELL HIM.
I'M SORRY, I'M SUPPOSED TO
TALK DRAMA TO YOU.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
BETTER?
THAT WAS THE LAST STRAW THAT
BROKE THE CAMEL'S BACK.
IT'S LIKE ARE YOU KIDDING
ME.
STRATEGICALLY KASS IS
PERFECT TO BRING TO THE END
BUT SHE'S SUCH AN INSULT TO
THIS GAME.
SO AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
WE'RE DONE.
TONY I WANT YOU TO NOW
THAT WHAT I DID WAS STRATEGIC.
I DON'T TRUST YOU TONY.
I KNOW THAT, THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM
YOU'RE OWN WORST ENEMY.
NOW ONE OF YOUR PEOPLE
DOESN'T KNOW IF HE'S ONE
OF YOUR PEOPLE.
WHAT ARE YOU DIGGING FOR NOW
PLEASE THAT'S ENOUGH.
LET ME CHECK TO SEE IF THAT TREE
IS RIPE WITH COCONUT.
I'M KIND OF OVER THE WHOLE TONY
THING,
BUT WU YOU NEEDED TO KNOW THAT
STUFF.
HE WAS GOING TO TAKE ME TO THE
FINAL THREE.
TO ME HE WAS PLAYING BOTH SIDES
WHEN HE TELLS WU SOMETHIING
AND HE TELLS ME THE SAME THING.
A TYPICAL STRATEGY WOULD BE TO
GET RID OF TONY,
BUT HE HAS AT LEAST ONE IDOL
THAT WE ARE AWARE OF,
PLUS HE'S SUCH A JERK I THINK I
CAN BEAT HIM IN THE END.
SO I THINK THE BEST OPTION FOR
ME AT THIS POINT
IS TO FILL IN WU AND SPENCER
AND SCRU UP TONY'S GAME.
AND HE REALLY DID PROMISE ON HIS
WIFE AND BABY WHICH I'M SURE
HE PROMISED YOU ON THE BOAT THE
OTHER DAY.
DID HE SWEAR ON HIS WIFE AND
BABY WITH YOU ON THE BOAT?
HE DIDN'T
WU DO YOU HAVE ANY THOUGHTS ON
THIS?
I DO THANK YOU!
NO YOU HAVE A GOOD ONE.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY HE MIGHT NOT.
I THINK HE REALLY WANT TO KEEP
ME BECAUSE
HE DOESN'T THINK I CAN WIN.
THAT'S WHY HE'S SO MAD.
>> I HAVE BEEN A CLOSE ALLY
WITH TONY PLAYING THIS GAME
WITH HIM SINCE DAY ONE.
BUT IT'S COME OUT THAT HE
PROMISED CASS ON HIS WIFE AN
BABY GIRL THAT HE WOULD TAKE
HER TO THE FINAL 3.
WHICH MEANS THAT I KNOW FOR
ALMOST FOR A FACT THAT TONY
WAS GOING TO BLINDSIDE ME SO
MY TRUST IN TONY HAS GONE
DOWN TREMENDOUSLY.
I MEAN WOO IF I GO OUT,
RIGHT, TONY AND TRISH ARE
DECIDING WHICH ONE OF YOU
GOES TO THE END WITH THEM
AND WHICH ONE OF THEM GOES
HOME.
>> THE QUESTION IS WHAT TO
DO ABOUT IT.
>> WELL, IF YOU WANT TO
INSURANCE YOU MAKE THE FINAL
3.
>> GET TRISH.
>> YEAH.
>> UH-HUH.
>> THIS MORNING I OVERHEARD
KASS SAYING I WAS A GO AND
THAT MAYBE THEY SHOULD VOTE
ME OUT.
WHICH REALLY INFURIATED ME
BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN SITTING
HERE TRYING TO BE NICE TO
KASS THIS WHOLE TIME WHICH
IS REALLY EXHAUSTING FOR ME.
BUT I WILL TELL YOU THIS,
SHE WILL BE SORRY SHE DID
THAT.
>> YOU AND I REALLY HAVE T
TO-- REPORT, ONE AND TWO.
>> GOING INTO TODAY MY GAME
WAS BASICALLY WIN IMMUNITY.
NOW THERE'S SOME CRACKS I
CAN WORK WITH WHICH APPEARS
TO BE GOOD NEWS BUT AT THE
SAME TIME I'M NOT STUPID.
I KNOW THAT I AM STILL
TARGET NUMBER ONE.
SO EVEN WITH EVERYTHING
GOING ON AT CAMP, I NEED
IMMUNITY.
AND I'M GOING TO FIGHT MY
ASS OFF FOR IT.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> GUYS READY TO GET TO
TODAY'S YOU MINE-- IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THING FIRST SPENCER,
TAKE BACK THE NECKLATION.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNE SIT BACK
UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE TO UNTANGLE A
BRAIDED ROPE RELEASING A
KEY.
YOU'LL THEN UNLOCK LADDER
RUNGS AND USE THEM TO BUILD
A LADDER.
YOU WILL THEN USE PLANKS TO
BUILD A STAIRCASE.
WHEN YOU REACH THE TOP, YOU
MUST-- THE SURVIVOR PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINCE
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE
IN FOUR SHOT AT WINNING THIS
GAME.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL, AFTER
36 DAYS SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT.
GET YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO FOR IMMUNITY, A
GUARANTEED SPOT IN THE FINAL
4.
SURVIVORS READY, GO.
FIRST STAGE VERY SIMPLE.
UNBRAID THE ROPE, THE KEY
WILL DROP.
GOT TO BE FULLY UNBRAIDED.
TONY DOING A NICE JOB OFF TO
A QUICK START.
GOT TO SEPARATE ALL THE
ROPES.
TRISH DOING A NICE JOB.
KASS MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS.
WOO AND SPENCER STRUGGLING.
TONY'S GOOD.
TONY HAS HIS KEY, HE CUN
LOCK THE LADDER RUNG.
BIG EARLY LEAD FOR TONY.
TONY HAS HIS RUNG FREE, HE'S
STARTING TO WORK ON HIS
LADDER.
TRISH, YOU'RE GOOD, TRISH.
KASS HAS HERS, GO, KASS.
>> SPENCER HAS IT.
GO SPENCER.
TRISH STARTING TO WORK ON
HER LADDER.
WOO IS THE LAST TO FINISH.
KASS, SPENCER IN IT, WOO NOW
IN ON IT.
THIS IS A LONG CHALLENGE.
DON'T PANIC, FOCUS.
YOU CAN ONLY PUT ONE RUNG UP
AT A TIME AND YOU HAVE TO GO
FROM THE BOTTOM TO THE TOP.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR
LADDERS.
TONY WITH A COUPLE OF
PIECES.
SPENCER HAS HIS SECOND
PIECE.
TRISH HAS HER FIRST PIECE.
IF YOU TRY TO FORCE IT AND
IT DOESN'T FIT, IT PROBABLY
DOESN'T BELONG THERE.
TONY WITH HIS THIRD PIECE.
TONY WITH HIS FOURTH PIECE.
TONY HAS BEEN LEADING THIS
CHALLENGE FROM THE BEGINNING.
TONY WITH HIS FIFTH PIECE.
SPENCER STILL LOOKING FOR
THAT THIRD PIECE.
TONY WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
KASS STILL WORKING ON HER
FIRST PIECE.
WOO LOOKING FOR THAT SECOND.
TONY HAS ONE PIECE LEFT ON
THE LADDER.
HE IS FLYING THROUGH THIS
CHALLENGE.
AND HE HAS GOT IT COMPLETED.
TONY NOW MOVING ON TO THE
STAIRCASE.
EXPERIENCE WE ARE HIS THIRD
PIECE.
TONY ALREADY WORKING ON THE
FLANKS.
HE'S GOT HIS FIRST.
SPENCER WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
TRISH, WOO AND KASS FALLING
OUT OF IT.
SPENCER DOWN TO TWO PIECES
LEFT.
TONY WITH ANOTHER PLANK.
EXPERIENCE WE ARE ANOTHER
RUNG, HE'S GOT ONE LEFT.
SPENCER HAS HIS LADDER
COMPLETED.
START WORKING ON THE PLANK,
THIS IS NOW TONY AND
SPENCER.
TONY WITH A BIG LEAD.
TONY WITH ANOTHER PLANK.
HE'S GOT ONE LEFT.
TONY NOW WORKING HIS WAY TO
THE TOP.
CAN START WORKING ON THAT
SLIDE PUZZLE, THE LAST PHASE
OF THIS CHALLENGE, THE ONLY
THING STANDING BETWEEN HIM
AND IMMUNITY, TONY HAS YET
TO WIN AN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
KASS, WOO AND TRISH HAVING A
TOUGH TIME BUILDING THAT
FIRST LADDER.
SPENCER'S ALMOST HALFWAY
THERE.
TONY SLIDES THE PIECES
AROUND.
TONY WITH A HUGE TIME
ADVANTAGE.
THE QUESTION IS DOES HE KNOW
HOW TO DO SLIDE PUZZLES.
WOO HAS HIS LADDER FINISHED.
KASS HAS HER LADDER
FINISHED.
ABSOLUTE DISASTER FOR TRISH.
TONY WORKING ON THE SLIDE
PUZZLE.
SLIDING PIECES ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
RAPIDLY.
DOES HE KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING
OR IS HE JUST LOST HIS MIND
AFTER 36 DAYS.
SPENCER WITH ANOTHER PLANK,
TWO LEFT.
ELSE'S GOT TO MOVE, TONY HAS
HAD A LOT OF TIME TO WORK ON
THIS SLIDE PUZZLE.
SFENSER WITH HIS NEXT TO
LAST PLANK.
SPENCER HAS ONE PLANK LEFT.
AN HE'S GOT IT.
SPENCER, START WORKING ON
YOUR SLIDE PUZZLE.
IT IS TONY AND SPENCER
WORKING ON THE PUZZLE, TONY
HAS LEAD THIS CHALLENGE FROM
THE BEGINNING, SPENCER HAS
WON IMMUNITY TWICE, HE KNOWS
HE WANTS IT AGAIN TONIGHT.
TONY HAS HAD A BIG LEAD
THROWING PIECES AROUND LIKE
A MADMAN, EXPERIENCE
CERTIFICATE STUDYING THE
PUZZLE.
TWO VERY DIFFERENT
APPROACHES.
TONY CONTINUES TO WORK AT A
FEVERISH PACE.
SPENCER VERY METHODICAL IN
HOW HE IS MOVING PIECES
AROUND.
BUT IT'S WORKING.
PUZZLE IS COMING TOGETHER.
TONY HUGE LEAD, SLIPPING WAY,
SPENCER HAS FOUND HIS WAY
BACK AND THIS WOULD BE A
HUGE COMEBACK.
>> SPENCER THINKS HE HAS IT.
AN INCREDIBLE COME BACK.
>> YES, YES LAM.
>> Jeff: SPENCER WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A SPOT
IN THE FINAL FOUR.
MASSIVE COMEBACK.
SPENCER, COME ON OVER YOU
SOLVED THAT SO FAST I BARELY
SAW IT HAPPEN.
>> I NEEDED IT.
SPENCER SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, GUARANTEED A
SPOT IN THE FINAL 4 CANNOT
BE VOTED OUT.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU AFTER
36 DAYS OUT HERE, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> SPENCER HAS ONE IMMUNITY,
ONCE AGAIN, SO NOW WE HAVE
TO SPEED UP THE PROCESS OF
ELIMINATION FROM OUR OWN
ALLIANCE.
WHICH IS GOING TO BE VERY,
VERY HARD
>> GOOD JOB, EVERYONE.
>> I COULDN'T GET THE THREE
RUNGS.
>> I NEVER DAY PUZZ NELL MY
LIFE.
I DON'T KNOW PUZZLES.
>> YOU GOT UP THERE QUICK.
>> YOU WERE LEADING, YEAH,
YOU WERE WAY AHEAD.
>> I KNEW I WASN'T GOING TO
DOT PUZZLE.
I COULD HAVE BEEN UP THERE
FOR AN HOUR, I WOULDN'T HAVE
GOT IT.
>> WINNING IMMUNITY DIDN'T
JUST FEEL GOOD T WAS
NIRVANA.
I MEAN THIS WAS A WIN OF
EPIC PROPORTIONS.
MY BACK WAS AGAINST THE WALL
I HAD TO WIN AND I DID.
AND NOW THAT I HAVE IMMUNITY
THESE FOUR ARE GOING HAVE TO
TURN ON EACH OTHER AND
CANNIBALIZE EACH OTHER AND
I'M JUST GOING TO SIT BACK
AND ENJOY THE SHOW.
>> IT'S BEEN GREAT, I THINK
YOU'RE A GREAT GUY, I JUST
VERY A QUICK QUESTION FOR
KASS, DO YOU THINK I'M
STUPID.
>> WHY WOULD I THINK I'M
>> OR DO YOU THINK I'M DPEF.
>> I KNEW YOU WERE LISTENING
TO THAT TRISH.
>> WHY WERE YOU SITTING
THERE TALKING ABOUT ME FIVE
FEET AWAY ABOUT HOW YOU WERE
GUNNING TO GET ME OFF.
>> YOU'RE TO THE GOING TO
DENY WHAT YOU SAID.
>> I DON'T HAVE THAT AGAINST
YOU.
>> IT'S TO THE BECAUSE I
DON'T LIKE YOU OR ANYTHING.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT I'M JUST LETTING YOU
KNOW WHAT KIND OF A GAME
KASS PLAYS, SHE PLAYS BOTH
SIDES AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
SHE'S THE VICTIM.
GO FIND SOMEONE WHO WILL
LISTEN YOUR VICTIM WOES
TODAY, BECAUSE I'M NOT.
>> I'M NOT A PASS OF A
GRESSIVE PERSON.
IF I HAVE A PROBLEM I GO
RIGHT TO THE SOURCE AND KASS
IS AN AGITATES TER, SHE
LOVES TO GET PEOPLE ANGRY AT
EACH OTHER.
AND THERE IS ONLY SOME OF
YOU CAN TAKE OF SOMEBODY
LIKE THAT.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO ARGUE
WITH ME.
I WILL RIP YOU APART IN 30
SECONDS.
>> STOP IT, GUYS.
>> YOU ARE A VICTIM, POOR ME,
EVERYONE IS PICKING ON ME
BUT YOU PLAY TWO SIDES TO
EVERYTHING.
THEN YOU TURN ON THAT BIG
YOU CAN LEE GRIN ON YOUR
FACE AND ACT LIKE YOU'RE
GOING WIN EVERYTHING.
AND I GOT NEWS FOR YOU,
SISTER, YOU'RE NOT.
>> TRISH WENT COMPLETELY OFF
THE HOOK WITH ME.
SHE LOOKED LIKE FRICKEN SKEL
TORE WITH HER BIG BLUE EYES
AND SKELETON FINGER WAVING
IN MY FACE.
YOU HAVE A VICIOUS AND CRUEL
HUMAN BEING.
AND EVERYONE SEES IT THE WAY
I DO, EXCEPT FOR YOU.
EVERYONE HERE SEES YOU FOR
WHO YOU ARE, SEPTEMBER FOR
YOU.
AND IT'S REALLY QUITE
TRAGIC.
>> TRISH, TACK A WALK.
>> TRISH IS PISSED OFF
BECAUSE OY THREW HER UNDER
THE BUS, WHICH IS PART OF
THE GAME SO GET OVER IT.
BUT THINGS GOT A LITTLE OUT
OF HAND TODAY.
I MEAN IT WAS GOING TO COST
ME MY GAME, IT COULD.
>> WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT.
>> IN IS WHY IT'S IMPORTANT
TO GET WOO BECAUSE WOO'S GO
GOING TO BE THE DECISION
MAKER HERE.
>> WOO KNOWS TONY'S PLAN.
>> YEAH BUT RIGHT NOW WHAT
THEY ARE DOING IS
CONSULTING.
>> THEY'RE SAYING LET'S VOTE
FOR KASS, I KNOW THAT.
>> IF THOSE THREE WHO JUST
WALKED OFF ARE TOGETHER
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
>> WE JUST NEED TO TALK TO
WOO.
WE REALLY NEED --
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS JUST BEFORE WE GO
ANY FURTHER, WOO, DO YOU
HAVE ANY QUESTIONS FOR ME.
ARE YOU QUESTIONING MY
INTEGRITY OR HONESTY?
ALL I WANT TO KNOW IS DID
YOU PROMISE HER ON YOUR WIFE
AND CHILD.
>> I DID THAT, I'M TO THE
GOING TO LIE TO YOU, BUT I
KNEW SHE ALREADY TRIED TO
BACK STAB ME THAT IS THE
ONLY REASON I DID THAT.
>> YOU NEVER SWORE TO ME
ABOUT TAKING ME TOP THREE
SO-- S THIS'S WHY I WAS
SKEPTICAL.
>> I PROMISED YOU BUT I
DIDN'T SWEAR, BUT NOW I'M
SWEARING TO YOU, SHE'S GONE.
>> TODAY I WAS DOING A LOT
OF SCRAMBLING A LOT MORE
LYING ALL BECAUSE KASS WENT
BLABBING HER MOUTH TO WOO
TELLING HIM I WAS TAKEN HER
TO THE FINAL THREE.
I DIDN'T MAKE ANY PROMISE TO
GO TO THE FINAL THREE AND
NOW HE IS SUSPICIOUS OF ME.
>> I'M JUST LIKE CONCERNED
JUST BECAUSE SHE CAME UP TO
ME.
>> I KNOW THAT.
YOU ME ANTHONY VOTE FOR KASS,
SHE IS GOES HOME.
>> I HAVE TWO IMMUNITY
IDOLS.
IF NOBODY FLIP APPROXIMATES
FROM THIS THREE IT IS
IMPOSSIBLE FOR THEM TO DO
ANYTHING.
KASS MIGHT BE A BEAUTIFUL
PERSON ON THE OUTSIDE WORLD,
BUT AS FAR AS SURVIVOR IS
CONCERNED, SHE IS ABSOLUTELY
HORRIBLE.
WHY WOULD SHE GO AND TELL
HIM THAT I SAID ALL THIS
STUFF UNLESS SHE WAS LOOKING
TO BLINDSIDE ME.
THEREFORE, SHE'S GOING HOME,
PERIOD.
>> WELL NOW WE'RE RIGHT HERE
AND I WILL SWEAR MY WIFE AND
MY KID IT'S ME, YOU AND
TRISH.
I SWEAR MY MOTHER, ON MY
DEAD DAD, I SWEAR ON HIS
GRAVE, ME, YOU AND TRISH ARE
GOING TO THE END, ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S TELEPHONE.
>> SO WE'RE VOTING KASS OFF
TONIGHT.
>> SHE'S GONE.
>> TONY HAS BEEN MAKING ALL
THESE PROMISES PRETTY MUCH
TO EVERYONE.
SO AT THIS POINT I JUST
DON'T FEEL AS THOUGH I CAN
TRUST HIM.
>> THAT'S IT, FINAL 3.
>> THE PROBLEM S I'M PRETTY
SURE THAT AT THE END OF THE
GAME, TONY IS GOING TO SE
SEE-- SAVE TRISH OVER ME SO,
I'M THINKING MAYBE IT'S TIME
TO MAKE THAT BIG MOVE.
>> WHAT'S UP WOO.
>>> YOU NEED HELP.
>> YEAH, SURE ALL RIGHT.
I JUST HAD.
>> YOU UNDERSTAND HOW IT
FEELS TRUST ME, ABUNDANTLY
CLEAR WOO CAME OVER AND SAID
WANT TO GET RID OF TRISH
WHICH WOULD YOU AWESOME,
UNFORTUNATELY I'M SKEPTICAL
BECAUSE HE HAS THE BEFORE
SAID HE WAS GOING TO DO
SOMETHING AND DECIDED NOT
TO.
SO I DON'T KNOW HOW SERIOUS
WOO IS ABOUT THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M LOOKING LONG TERM FOR
MYSELF AND FOR HIM TO COME
UP TO KASS AND MAKE THE
INITIATIVE OF BLINDSIDING ME,
POTENTIALLY TRISH AND TONY
ARE INSEPARABLE.
AND IF YOU OR I WANT A SHOT
AT WINNING WE HAVE TO HAVE A
SHOT AT VOTING TONY OUT AT
THE FINAL FOUR.
AND WE CAN'T DO THAT IF FISH
IS HERE.
>> THAT'S WHAT IM 'S SAYING.
I'M PRETTY MUCH SET ON
VOTING TRISH, IF I VOTE OUT
TRISH CAN WE MAKE A PACT
THAT WE WILL GO FINAL 3.
>> YES NO MATTER WHAT.
>> COOL?
>> I'M THE SWING VOTE AT
THIS POINT.
I CAN EITHER GET RID OF
TRISH OR TAKE OUT KASS.
I HAVEN'T MADE UP MY MIND AT
THIS POINT.
I'M STILL TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT OPTION IS GOING TO
BE THE BEST FOR ME SO I GOT
TO MAKE A HUGE DECISION AND
TIME TIME IS TICKING.
>> I JUST SAW WOO TALKING TO
EXPERIENCE AND KASS AND I'M
THINKING TO MYSELF WHAT THE
HELL JUST HAPPENED.
I THOUGHT WE WERE A STRONG
ALLIANCE.
YOU KNOW IS AN INJUSTICE TO
BRING THAT GIRL TO THE TOP,
MAN.
YOU KNOW IS.
I SWEAR TO YOU ON MY DAD'S
GRAVE BECAUSE I KNEW I
WASN'T GOING BREAK IT WITH
YOU.
I NEED YOU.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE THAT ME
AND WOO ARE ON THE SAME
PAGE.
IF NOT, I MIGHT HAVE TO
BREAK MY PROMISE AND CHANGE
THE PLAN.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
>> WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY SAR A
MORGAN, LJ, JEREMIAH, JEFFRA
AND TASHA VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT SO, INTERESTING
SITUATION TONIGHT, TONY.
SPENCER WINCE IMMUNITY, WE
FINALLY GET TO THE GOOD
PART.
ONE OF THE FOUR OF YOU ARE
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> WELL, THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
IT'S GOING TO BE, JEFF,
CHALLENGE BEAST WON IMMUNITY
ONCE AGAIN, HIS BACK WAS UP
AGAINST THE WALL AND GAVE IT
HIS BEST AND HE PREVAILED.
>> Jeff: KASS, WHAT WAS THE
VIBE AT CAMP AFTER THE
CHALLENGE.
>> THE MINUTE WE GOT BACK
TRISH RAILED INTO ME LIKE A
FRICKING WILD SKELETON BLUE
EYED BAN CHI.
>> Jeff: WHAT WAS THAT
AGAIN.
>> I DONE EVEN KNOW WHAT I
SAID BUT I'M SURE IT WAS
ACCURATE.
SHE WAS YELLING AT ME,
TELLING ME I WAS AGAINST HER
AND JUST SHOWING HER
CAPACITY FOR HATRED AND SHE
WAS HOLDING THIS IN UNTIL
SHE KNEW SPENCER WON BECAUSE
WE WEREN'T ABLE TO VOTE OUT
SPENCER.
>> TRISH, ONE PHRASE IN
THERE, YOUR CAPACITY FOR
HATRED.
>> YEAH.
KASS UNFORTUNATELY IS ALWAYS
THE VICTIM.
AND SHE LIKES TO BE A
TROUBLEMAKER BUT THEN SHE
DOESN'T LIKE CONFLICT.
IF GRUING TO BE AN AGITATOR
AND PLOT WOO AGAINST TONY
AND TONY AGAINST WOO, DON'T
SIT BACK AND SAY BUT I
DIDN'T DO EVERYTHING.
NOW EVERYBODY IS BEING SO
MEAN TO ME.
SHE HAS A FIGHT WITH ALMOST
EVERYBODY EVERY SINGLE DAY.
>> I HAVEN'T FOUGHT WITH
ANYBODY ON THE JURY.
I HAVEN'T EVEN HAD A
CONFRONTATION WITH ANYONE
OUTSIDE OF KASS TODAY.
>> INSTEAD YOU JUST RAIL
INTO SOMEBODY.
I SEE, I SEE.
>> Jeff: SPENCER.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THIS IS GREAT FOR
YOU BECAUSE ANY TIME SOMEONE
ELSE IS CRUMBLING IT'S AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR SOMEONE
ELSE.
>> I MEAN THINGS WERE PRETTY
CRAZY TODAY.
AND THE FACT THAT I WON
IMMUNITY SPED UP THIS
PROCESS OF THE FOUR HAVING
TO TURN ON EACH OTHER.
>> WOO, DOES THIS BREAK YOUR
HEART A LITTLE BIT TO SEE
PEOPLE ARGUING OR IS THIS
STRATEGY WISE FANTASTIC FOR
YOU?
>> WELL, IT'S EVIDENT THAT
THERE HAS BEEN HIDDEN
VENDETTA AND ANIMOSITY AND
WHEN THESE CONFRONTATION
GOES ON, OUR FOURSOME BREAKS
UP.
NOW I LOOK AT IT AS THREE
BRAWN VERSUS TWO BRAIN.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE PUTTING KASS
BACK WITH SPENCER.
>> IT'S PRETTY CLEAR.
AND THAT PUTS KASS IN A VERY
VULNERABLE POSITION.
>> Jeff: KASS, DOES THAT
SHOCK YOU, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
BEEN CLEAR ABOUT SAYING I AM
NOT WITH THEM, I AM WITH YOU
GUYS.
>> I DIDN'T PREDICT THAT
PSYCHO BITCH WOULD COME OUT
AT ME TODAY BUT TONY WAS
CAUSE TRYING TO TELL ME I'M
FINAL THREE AN WOO IS FINAL
THREE.
>> IN YOUNG LADY IS
DELUSIONA.
THIS IS WHAT HAD.
WOO APPROACHES ME AND SAYS
KASS IS TALKING TO SPENCER,
THEY WANT TO BLINDSIDE.
I GO UP TO KASS AND SAY
LET'S BE COOL, WE CAN MAKE
IT TO THE END.
BUT IT IS BETWEEN US, BLAH,
BLAH, BLAH, SHE GOES BACK TO
CAMP, WOO, IS IT TRUE YOU
TOLD TONY THIS AND THAT.
I SAID KASS YOU JUST SEALED
YOUR FATE WHY WOULD YOU TELL
HIM WHAT I TOLD YOU IF WE
ARE WORKING TOGETHER.
>> THE WOO EXCHANGE WORKED
OUT AS I THOUGHT WAS.
>> Jeff: SHE PLANNED THIS
ALL ALONG.
>> TONY SAID KASS THE DEAL
IS OFF, I'M DONE WITH YOU,
IT'S OVER, IN FRONT OF WOO
WHO HE HAD A DEAL WITH.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL WOO.
SO TONY IN BEING SO
ANGRY-- .
>> I'M EMOTIONAL.
I EXPRESS MY FEELINGS AND MY
EXPRESSIONAL-- EXPRESSIONS.
SHE SITS WITH THE SAME GRIN,
MAD, HAPPY, SMILING, CRYING,
SAME LOOK THERE IT IS.
>> WELL, YOU'RE MAKING AN
ASS OF MYSELF.
>> AND SHE CALLS ME AN
ANIMAL SO I HAVE TO TALK TO
HER LIKE I'M AN ANIMAL SO
SHE CAN UNDERSTAND ME IT IS
JUST A JOKE W WE ARE HERE TO
PLAY A GAME.
LET'S HAVE FUN WITH IT.
>> Jeff: WOW.
ISN'T THIS AWESOME?
SPENCER, YOU SEEM SORT OF
DISGUSTED BY IT.
I WOULD THINK YOU WOULD BE
CHUCKLING.
>> I DO FIND IT FUNNY, I
JUST FEEL LIKE I'M IN ONE
FLEW OVER THE CUCKOO'S NEST.
>> AND IT'S MEDICATION TIME.
>> IT'S JUST NUTS.
>> Jeff: WOO WHAT IS YOUR
TAKE.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M STUCK IN
THE WORST FAMILY POSSIBLE
WITH TONY BEING DAD AND
TRISH BEING THE MOM, KASS
BEINGED SISTER AND SPENCER
BEING THE SON AND I'M JUST
LIKE THAT FOREIGN EXCHANGE
STUDENT WHO IS SHOCKED EVERY
SINGLE TIME IT GOES DOWN.
YOU WANT TO COME OUT AND
TELL THESE GUYS JUST TO SHUT
UP AND CONSENSUS-- CONCENTRATE
MORE SO ON THE GAME.
>> Jeff: I DON'T REMEMBER A
TRIBAL COUNCIL THIS LATE IN
THE GAME WHERE THERE WERE
THIS MANY PEOPLE LAUGHING
EVEN THOUGH SOMEBODY'S DREAM
IS GOING TO FALL THREE DAYS
SHORT IN JUST A FEW FEW
MINUTES.
>> JECH, TONIGHT'S VOTE IS
TO THE GOING TO BE EMOTIONAL,
IT IS GAME PLAY THAT IS ALL
IT.
I'M DEFINITELY NOT GOING
HOME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: WHY DOW SAY YOU'RE
DEFINITELY TO THE GOING
HOME.
>> WELL, JEFF-- MY BAG OF
TRICKS IS GETTING TOO HEAVY
FOR ME SO TONIGHT IT IS
GOING TO BE OUT WITH THE OLD,
WHICH I'M GOING GET RID OF
TONIGHT AND IN WITH THE NEW,
JEFF.
NEW SPECIAL ONE RIGHT HERE.
>> Jeff: WOW, BIG REACTION.
FIVE PEOPLE LEFT, I HAVE TO
USE IT AND IN MY SPECIAL I
HAVE ANOTHER SURPRISE WITH
THEM WHEN I USE THIS IDOL,
JEFF, AND I WON'T DISCLOSE
THAT EITHER AS OF NOW.
>> Jeff: SPENCER WHAT IS
YOUR TAKE ON IT.
>> NORMALLY I WOULD POINT
OUT THE BIGGEST THREAT RIGHT
NOW TO WIN THE GAME, TONY,
AND CASTING MY VOTE THAT
WAY.
>> CAN'T TOUCH ME THOUGH.
>> BUT THIS COMPLICATES
THINGS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS
TIME TO VOTE.
KASS, YOU'RE UP.
>>> I SUGGEST A BOOK ON
SELF-AWARENESS.
IT WILL BE HENFUL FOR YOU IN
THE FUTURE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ANYBODY HAVE A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT
TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE
TIME TO DO SO.
>> I DON'T NEED TO PLAY IT
BUT I HAVE NO USE FOR THIS
THING.
IT STAYS ON THE ISLAND.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST TONY
WILL NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, TRISH.
>> KASS.
TRISH, TWO VOTES TRISH, ONE
VOTE KASS.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT, THE
7th MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
TRISH, 3 IS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
>> Jeff: TRISH, ITS TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU HAVE MADE
IT TO THE FINAL FOUR, GIVEN
THE HISTORY OF EVENTS THUS
FAR T IS ANYBODY'S GAME TO
WIN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> NEXT TIME ON ITS TWO HOUR
SEASON FINALE OF SURVIVOR.
>> YOU WANT ME TO COME OUT
AND BE YOUR MAMA OR COME OUT
AND WIN.
>> THE ROAD TO THE END IS
NEVER EASY.
>> IF IT COMES DOWN TO ME
BURNING THE WHL PLACE DOWN
JOIN US FOR THE FINALE.
>> YOU KNOW I MAY BE TOO
NICE TO PLAY THIS GAME BUT
FROM KASS PERSPECTIVE
MAYBE-- IT IS STRESSFUL,
FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE TO BACK
STAB.
I'M GRATEFUL FOR WHAT I HAVE
AND LOOKING FORWARD TO
GETTING BACK TO IT.
PEANUT M & Ms, ANYONE.
I'M SO FRICKING HUNGRY.