>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN,
"SURVIVOR" IS TAKING
TELEVISION'S GREATEST SOCIAL
EXPERIMENT IN A NEW DIRECTION.
THESE 18 AMERICANS HAVE BEEN
DIVIDED INTO THREE GROUPS THAT
REPRESENT THE QUALITIES THEY
MOST RELY ON IN THEIR DAILY
LIVES.
THE BRAIN TRIBE, WITH AN AVERAGE
I.Q. OF 130, THIS GROUP UTILIZES
THEIR INTELLECT TO ACCOMPLISH
THEIR GOALS.
>> IN 2010, I ENTERED THE WORLD
OPEN CHESS TOURNAMENT, AND I
TIED FOR FIRST.
I CERTAINLY DON'T LOOK
DIABOLICAL OR LIKE A GENIUS,
BOTH OF WHICH I AM.
>> I'M PRESIDENT OF THE MIAMI
MARLINS.
IN BASEBALL, THERE'S ONLY ONE
WINNER AT THE END.
"SURVIVOR" IS THE SAME.
SO I'VE BEEN PLAYING THIS GAME
FAIR LONG TIME, JUST NOT ON THE
BEACH.
>> I AM AN ATTORNEY, AND MY
TRACK RECORD IS UNDEFEATED.
THEY THINK, HOW CUTE, THERE'S
THE MOM.
THEY DON'T KNOW I'M PROBABLY
MORE CUNNING AND RUTHLESS THAN
95% OF THE POPULATION.
>> Jeff: THE BEAUTY TRIBE.
THIS GROUP INCLUDES A
CHEERLEADER, PANELLENT QUEEN,
AND FASHION MOD WHOLE RELY ON
THEIR LOOKS TO GET WHAT THEY
WANT.
>> I WAS AN NFL CHEERLEADER.
I DON'T WANT TO SOUND LIKE
SUPER-CONCEITED BUT FROM A GUY I
USUALLY GET WHAT I WANT.
>> I'M A FASHION MODEL.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO HELP ME
OUT GET A LITTLE BIT FURTHER
INTO THE GAME BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO WIN THEM OVER WITH MY LOOKS.
>> I COMPETED IN MISS KENTUCKY.
I WAS SECOND PLACE THREE YEARS
IN A ROW.
I BELIEVE BEAUTY IS GOING TO
HELP ME WITH THE SOCIAL ASPECT
OF THE GAME.
>> Jeff: THE BRAWN TRIBE.
THIS GROUP RELIES ON PHYSICAL
STRENGTH.
>> MY NAME IS CLIFF ROBINSON.
I PLAYED 18 YEARS IN THE N.B.A.
I ALWAYS PLAY FOR BREAD AND
MEAT.
I DON'T WIN, I DON'T EAT.
THAT'S WHAT THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" IS ABOUT.
>> I'M A POLICE OFFICER.
AND I STARTED MIXED MARTIAL ARTS
IN 2009.
GETTING PAID TO PUNCH SOMEONE IN
THE FACE, IT DOESN'T REALLY GET
BETTER THAN THAT.
>> I'VE BEEN A POLICE OFFICER IN
JERSEY CITY FOR 13 YEARS.
I'M ALWAYS JUMPING OVER CARS,
FROM ROOF TO ROOF CHASING
PEOPLE.
SO THIS GAME TO ME SHOULD BE
EASY.
KNOCK ON WOOD.
>> Jeff: IT IS THE ULTIMATE
CHALLENGE-- BRAWN VERSUS BRAINS
VERSUS BEAUTY.
WHICH TRAIT WILL PROVE THE MOST
VALUABLE?
>> I'M SUPER SMART.
I HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO WIN THIS
GAME.
>> I DON'T SEE THE GUYS GOING,
"OH, I WANT TO VOTE HER OFF
RIGHT AWAY."
THEY DON'T WANT TO LOOK AT UGLY
GIRLS ALL DAY.
>> CHAIM KNOWN AS THE TOUGH
BRAWNY GIRL.
WHEN I FEEL LIKE SOMEONE'S OUT
TO GET ME, I'M GOING TO GET YOU
BACK AND I'M GOING TO GET YOU 10
TIMES HARDER.
>> Jeff: AND WHO WILL HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES TO OUTLAST ALL THE
REST?
>> I WILL GO DOWN AS ONE OF THE
BEST PLAYERS TO PLAY, AND I WANT
TO PLAY AN AWESOME GAME.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, ONLY ONE
WILL REMAIN TO CLAIM THE
MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 18 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
>> I AM SO EXCITED TO START
"SURVIVOR, I CAN'T EVEN STAND.
I'M SUCH A COMPETITIVE PERSON I
WOULD LITERALLY DO ANYTHING TO
GET TO THE FINISH LINE TO BEAT
YOU IF I HAD TO.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST WHO I AM.
>> WHEN I SAW THE SPEED BOAT
RACE UP, THE GIRLS WERE IN THE
FRONT AND THEY WERE ALL KIND OF
LIKE OH, LOOK AT US.
I'M SURPRISED THERE WASN'T,
LIKE, CHEESY MUSIC IN THE
BACKGROUND.
>> I'VE NOTICED A FEW PEOPLE
COMING OFF THE HELICOPTER WHO
SEEM LIKE MORE OF THE NERDY
TYPE, LIKE THE COCHRAN OF THE
GAME THAT'S GOING TO BE REALLY
SMART AND WITTY AND PLAY THE
GAME WELL.
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR:
CAGAYAN."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
YOU'VE BEEN DIVIDED INTO THREE
TRIBES BASED ON THREE OF THE
QUALITIES IT TAKES TO SUCCEED IN
THIS GAME: BRAWN, BRAINS, AND
BEAUTY.
THE WOMAN IN THE BLACK, WHAT'S
YOUR NAME?
>> MORGAN.
>> Jeff: MORGAN.
JUST LOOKING AT THE MIXTURE
HERE, IF YOU HAD TO CHOOSE, WHAT
WOULD YOU SAY YOU GUYS ARE, THE
BEAUTY, THE BRAINS, OR THE
BRAWN?
>> I MEAN, I DON'T MEAN TO SOUND
CONCEITED BUT I THINK WE'RE BY
THEY.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: LET'S GO DOWN HERE TO
THE END.
GUY IN THE BACK, GREEN.
IF THEY'RE BEAUTY, WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU FIT IN?
>> I GUESS WE'RE THE NERDS.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: BASED ON WHAT?
>> OH, BASED ON THEM LOOKING
REALLY PHYSICAL.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: THAT LEAVES THE GROUP
IN THE MIDDLE.
YOU GUYS MUST BE BRAWN.
THE GUY IN THE GRAY T-SHIRT,
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> TONY.
>> Jeff: DOES THAT FEEL ALL
RIGHT TO YOU?
DO YOU ACCEPT THAT?
>> I GLADLY ACCEPT THAT.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU LIKE
ABOUT BEING IN THE BRAWN TRIBE?
>> WE'RE GOING TO STOMP ON
BEAUTY AND WE'RE GOING TO STOMP
ON SMART.
I LOVE IT.
>> Jeff: THIS SEASON IS GOING
TO TEST YOUR ABILITY TO DRAW ON
DIFFERENT PARTS OF BRAWN,
BRAINS, AND BEAUTY WHILE YOU
ADAPT IN THIS GAME MOMENT BY
MOMENT, STARTING RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE GOING TO CHOOSE A LEADER
FROM EACH TRIBE.
IF YOU HAVE NOT HAD A CHANCE TO
TALK, REALLY ALL YOU CAN DO IS
SIZE EACH OTHER UP BY LOOKING AT
EACH OTHER.
WE'LL START DOWN HERE ON THE END
WITH BEAUTY.
FIGURE IT OUT.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO REPRESENT
TRIBE?
THE GUY IN THE BLACK HAT, IT
LOOKS LIKE IT'S.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
>> L.J.
>> Jeff: HOW DOES IT FEEL
MOMENTS INTO THIS GAME YOU'VE
BEEN SELECTED AS THE GUY TO
REPRESENT THE HOT TRIBE.
>> CLEARLY I'M THE INNER BEAUTY
OF THE GROUP.
IF I'M THE MAN THAT STICKS OUT,
WE HAVE TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: LET'S GO HERE IN THE
MIDDLE TO THE BRAWN.
WHO'S IS GOING TO BE?
>> SARAH.
>> Jeff: SARAH IN THE FRONT.
THE WOMAN IN THE YELLOW, WHAT'S
YOUR NAME?
>> TRISH.
>> Jeff: TRISH.
WHY SARAH?
>> SHE'S PRETTY CONFIDENT.
SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE CAN GET THE
JOB DONE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
DOWN TO THE THIRD TRIBE.
WHO IS GOING TO REPRESENT THE
BRAIN TRIBE?
>> WHO LOOKS THE SMARTEST.
( LAUGHTER )
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YOU GUYSMENT ME, I'M YOURS.
>> THERE WE GO.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> DAVID.
>> Jeff: OKAY, WOMAN ON THE
END, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> KASS.
>> Jeff: KASS, WHY DAVID?
I.
>> I PERSONALLY NEVER TRUST A
MAN IN A SUIT BUT I TRUST DAVID
SO WE'LL GO WITH THAT.
>> Jeff: SO WE HAVE OUR THREE
LEADERS.
NOW THE GAME IS GOING TO GET A
LITTLE TOUGHER.
THE LEADERS OF EACH GROUP ARE
NOW GOING TO DECIDE WHO IS THE
WEAKEST FROM THEIR GROUP.
IF YOU HAVE TO GET RID OF
SOMEBODY, WHO DO YOU GET RID OF?
SUDDENLY, BEING THE LEADER IS
NOT THE POSITION YOU WANT TO BE
IN.
L.J., WE'RE GOING TO START WITH
YOU.
>> THIS GAME IN THE BEGINNING IS
ALL PHYSICAL CHALLENGES.
AND I THINK IF I HAD TO, I WOULD
HAVE TO PICK MORGAN.
>> Jeff: MORGAN.
WOW.
THIS CAN'T HAPPEN OFTEN TO YOU
IN LIFE.
>> FIRST FOR EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: TAKE A STEP OVER
HERE, MORGAN.
>> IN MY PERSPECTIVE OF BEAUTY,
THERE IS HOT AND THERE'S CUTE.
MORGAN, SHE'S HOT.
WHEREAS THE OTHER GIRLS ARE,
LIKE, CUTE, AND ME, PERSONALLY,
I TRUST CUTE MORE THAN I TRUST
HOT.
>> Jeff: LET'S GO TO THE BRAWN
TRIBE NOW.
SARAH, BASED ON FIRST
IMPRESSIONS, WHO DO YOU DUMP
FROM THIS TRIBE?
>> I'VE GOT A GOOD VIBE FROM
EVERYONE.
I MEAN, THIS IS A REAL SUCKY
POSITION.
BUT I GUESS WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
THE WOMAN IN THE YELLOW.
>> Jeff: TRISH, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: TRISH, YOU WERE THE
FIRST PERSON TO SPEAK UP FOR
SARAH.
AND SHE'S THE ONE WHO ULTIMATELY
PUTS YOU OUT.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
IF THAT'S HOW SHE FEELS, THAT'S
HOW SHE FEELS.
GLRT, WE NEED ONE MORE.
DOWN TO THE BRAIN TRIBE.
DAVID, BECAUSE OF YOUR JACKET,
EVIDENTLY, YOU WERE SELECTED AS
THE LEADER OF THIS GROUP.
>> JUST FOR THE RECORD, THE
JACKET DOESN'T MATCH THE PANTS,
SO IT'S NOT A SUIT.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU USED TO
MAKING DECISIONS LIKE THIS,
DAVID?
>> I MAKE DECISIONS LIKE THIS
OFTEN, AND I'M GOING TO GO WITH
HIM.
>> Jeff: WOW, YOU DIDN'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT IT.
GUY IN THE GREEN, WHAT'S YOUR
NAME.
>> GARRET.
>> Jeff: DAVID.
>> WOULD JUST SAY FROM STANDING
HERE, THAT IS A SURPRISING
CHOICE.
WHAT DID YOU BASE IT ON?
>> FOCUSING ON I'D SAY THE LAST
TWO-THIRD OF THE GAME.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE ALREADY
LOOKING TO THE END.
>> WELL, YOU ASKED ME TO MAKE A
DECISION FOR NOW, BUT EVERY
DECISION YOU MAKE IS BASED ON
WHAT'S GOOD FOR NOW AND WHAT'S
GOOD FOR LATER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GARRET,
TAKE A SPOT OVER HERE NEXT TO
TRISH.
>> MY STRATEGY WITH CHOOSING
GARRET IS HE'S BUILT LIKE A MACK
TRUCK, AND HE'S GOT BRAINS, TOO?
NOW, THAT'S GOING TO BE A
FORMIDABLE COMBINATION.
SO I FIGURED IT WOULD MAKE SENSE
TO GET RID OF HIM.
>> Jeff: THIS IS HOW FAST
"SURVIVOR" CHANGES.
IF THIS HAD BEEN A TRIBAL
COUNCIL, ALL THREE OF YOU,
MORGAN, TRISH, GARRET, WOULD BE
OUT OF THIS GAME.
FORTUNATELY, FOR YOU, IT'S NOT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU'RE NOT OUT OF THE GAME.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN OUT OF YOUR
TRIBE, BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
GO BACK TO CAMP WITH THEM.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET ON THE
CHOPPER.
YOU'RE GOING TO FLY AHEAD.
YOU WILL LAND AT CAMP EARLY, AND
YOU WILL MAKE A DECISION ON
BEHALF OF THE TRIBE THAT JUST
VOTE YOU OUT.
NOW, IT'S THE THREE TRIBES THAT
ARE WORRIED, WONDERING WHAT DID
WE JUST DO?
GRAB YOUR BAGS, GET ON THE
CHOPPER.
GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FOR THE
REST OF YOU, I HAVE MAPS TO YOUR
NEW HOME.
( APPLAUSE )
BEAUTY TRIBE.
YOU ARE SALANA.
BRAWN, YOU ARE APARE.
BRAINS, YOU ARE LUZAN.
GOOD NEWS IS YOU HAVE GREAT
WEATHER ON DAY ONE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD TO YOUR
NEW CAMP, GET STARTED ON
BUILDING SHELTER.
IT COULD BE A WET SEASON.
GOOD LUCK.
>> TO BE ISOLATED FROM THE GROUP
RIGHT AWAY, IT REALLY SUCKS.
LIK>> LIKE AT LEAST BOTH OF THE
OTHER TWO LEADERS PREPPEDDED
THEY WERE SO SAD TO HAVE TO PICK
THE PERSON, BUT DAVID DOESN'T
HESITATE.
HE IMMEDIATELY PATS ME ON THE
BACK AND SAYS, "GARRET."
HE IS THE WEAKEST.
WHICH IS B.S.
I'M STRONGER THAN ANY OF THEM.
THERE IT IS.
"YOU HAVE A DECISION TO MAKE.
YOU CAN HELP YOURSELF OR HELP
YOUR TRIBE."
ALL RIGHT, WE CAN JUST "X" THIS
SECOND PART OUT.
I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO BE
HELPING MYSELF.
IF YOU CHOOSE TO HELP YOUR
TRIBE, YOU'LL BE GIVEN A SECOND
BAG OF RICE.
IF YOU CHOOSE TO HELP YOURSELF,
YOU'LL BE GIVEN THE CLUE TO THE
LOCATIONAVE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED I'M
ALREADY ON THE OUTS WITH MY
TRIBE SO THIS IS A COMPLETE
NO-BRAINER.
OBVIOUSLY, I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
SEE WHAT WE'VE GOT HERE.
STRAIGHT FORWARD.
WHEN PEOPLE SEE MY BODY, OFTEN
THEY'RE LIKE, "HE'S JUST A DUMB
JOCK!"
BUT I WAS VALEDICTORIAN OF NIGH
CLASS, 99 PERCENTILE S.A.IT IS,
AND FOR A LIVING I'M A
HIGH-STAKES PROFESSIONAL POKER
PLAYER.
SO ANYTHING I DO IN MY LIFE, I
GO ALL IN.
"FIND THE PLACE WHERE WATER'S
FALLING."
SO GO TO THE WATER FALL.
WITHOUT QUESTION, DAVID MAKE THE
ASININE DECISION HE DID WORKS TO
MY ADVANTAGE, BUT HE'S A THREAT,
AND I WANT HIM OUT OF THE GAME.
>> WHEN SARAH HAD TO PICK THE
WEAK OF THE TRIBE, WHEN I LOOKED
AROUND, I WAS CLEARLY THE OLD
OLDEST.
I WAS CLEARLY THE THINNEST, SO I
WASN'T SURPRISED IT WAS ME.
"IF YOU CHOOSE TO HELP YOURSELF
YOU'LL BE GIVEN THE CLUE TO A
LOCATION OF--" OH, CRAP!
SHOOT!
WHEN I SAW THAT NOTE, I WAS LIKE
OH, GEEZ.
I'VE GOT TO MAKE A DECISION
WHETHER IT'S FOR ME OR THE TEAM.
INITIALLY, I COULD HEAR MYSELF
SAYING, "DON'T BE AN IDIOT.
GO AND GET THE IDOL FOR YOURSELF
AND PROTECT YOURSELF."
GOD, I'M SO NOT SELFISH, BUT
MAYBE I NEED TO BE.
I HAVE BEEN DIVORCED FOR 15
YEARS, SUPPORTING AND RAISING MY
CHILDREN EMOTIONALLY AND
FINANCIALLY, AND IT'S BEEN
REALLY HARD.
YET, AT THE SAME TIME, I HAVE
ALWAYS BEEN A TEAM PLAYER.
IT'S JUST WHO I AM.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GO WITH HELPING THE
GROUP.
I'M GOING TO PASS UP THE IDOL.
I JUST WENT WITH MY GUT AND
SAID,UN WHAT?
I'M JUST GOING TO GO WITH THE
TEAM.
I HOPE I DON'T KICK MYSELF FOR
THE REST OF THE GAME ON THAT
ONE, BUT THERE'S NOTHING I CAN
DO NOW.
SO I JUST HOPE I DON'T REGRET
IT.
>> I'M SURPRISED.
I WAS VOTED OFF FIRST.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE MORE PHYSICAL
STRENGTH THAN THE OTHER TWO
LADIES, AND I KIND OF THOUGHT I
HAD THE GUYS UNDER MY THUMB.
BUB MAYBE L.J. WAS TEMPTED BY MY
LOOKS AND DEPARTMENT WANT ME
AROUND.
IT MESSED WITH HIS HEAD.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOOD AT.
MAYBE HE CAN SENSE THAT.
I HOLD GRUDGES BIG TIME.
I WILL NEVER FORGIVE HIM FOR
THIS.
"TAKE A STROLL ALONG THE ROCKS."
THIS IS A GAME WHERE YOU HAVE TO
SAVE YOURSELF, SO OF COURSE I'M
GOING TO LOOK FOR THE IDOL.
I GUESS I'M A SELFISH PERSON,
BUT IF I CAN FIND IT, IT'S GOING
TO BE A HUGE GAME CHANGER FOR
SURE.
>> CLEARLY GOING TO HAVE TO GET
DOWN AND DIRT INTO THIS WATER.
THE CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL SAID IT'S RIGHT BY THE
WATER FALL.
UNFORTUNATELY THESE HIDE AND GO
SEEK ACTIVITIES IS NOT MY AREA
OF EXPERTISE.
I'VE BEEN IN THE SITUATION AT A
POKER TABLE PLAYING FOR HUGE
AMOUNTS OF MONEY, AND I DIDN'T
GET STRESSED OUT ABOUT IT.
SO THIS SHOULD BE CHILD'S PLAY.
I'M EXWARGS MYSELF BY NOT BEING
ABLE TO FIND THE STUPID IDOL
RIGHT NOW.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'S THIS?
I FEEL SOMETHING!
WHAT IS THIS?
>> LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT IN
HERE.
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL!
OH!
FINALLY, I WAS ABLE TO FIND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO KEEP IT
TO MYSELF.
BUT WHAT AN AMAZING START TO THE
GAME.
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL WILL
KEEP YOU SAFE FROM BEING VOTED
OFF AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ME HAVING THE IDOL PUT ME IN A
REALLY STRONG POSITION.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL DAVID
WAS THINKING, BUT I PROMISE YOU,
I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING IN MY
POWER TO GET RID OF HIM.
>> THE CLUE SAID THAT THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL WOULD BE SOMEWHERE
NEAR ROCKS.
SO IMMEDIATELY, I THOUGHT OF THE
HUGE ROCK SHELF TO THE RIGHT OF
OUR CAMP.
THERE ARE SO MANY LITTLE
CREVICES AND NOOKS AND CRANNIES
THAT THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
COULD BE HIDDEN BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHEN THEY'RE GOING TO BE HERE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH TIME I
HAVE.
I JUST KNOW THAT I HAVE TO FIND
IT.
>> WHEN WE ARRIVED AT THE BEACH
IT'S LIKE, WHERE'S MORGAN?
SHE WAS NOWHERE TO BE FOUND AND
IT WAS JUST VERY SUSPICIOUS.
>> I WAS CLIMBING ON THE ROCKS,
THEN I SAW MY OTHER TRIBE MATES
COME STROLLING UP ON THE BEACH,
AND MY HEART JUST JUMPED IN MY
THROAT.
IF I HAD BEEN OUTED TRYING TO
FIND THE IDOL, AND I THOUGHT I
HAVE TO COME UP WITH SOMETHING
OR I'M GOING HOME FOR SURE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS OUR HUMBLE ABODY.
I WONDER WHERE MORGAN IS.
>> MY OTHER TRIBEMATES COME
STROLLING UP ON THE BEACH.
IT WAS PRETTY OBVIOUS WHAT I WAS
DOING.
I HAD ALREADY BEEN OUTED AS THE
WEAKEST PERSON AND NOW I'M GOING
BEHIND THEIR BACKS AND TRYING TO
FIND THE IDOL.
I'M LIKE I'M DONE.
>> I WONDER WHAT DECISION SHE
HAD TO MAKE.
>> THEN I REALIZED I COULD JUST
TOTALLY LIE AND SAY THAT, "OH,
YEAH, I PICKED THE SHELTER
MATERIAL AND FISHING STUFF OVER
COMFORT.
>> HERE SHE COMES.
>> I HOPE YOU GUYS LIKES WHAT I
PICKED.
>> WHAT DID YOU GET TO DECIDE?
>> I PICKED RICE, SHELTER STUFF,
AND FISHING.
>> GOOD CHOICE.
>> I FOR SURE THINK I FOOLED
THEM.
NOW I HAVE HOWEVER MANY DAYS TO
LOOK FOR THE IDOL.
I'LL HAVE TO BE REALLY SLY ABOUT
IT BUT I DON'T THINK THEY HAVE
ANY CLUE.
THERE ARE TIDE POOLS.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS CHECKING OUT.
>> MORGAN IS ALREADY IN HER
UNDERWEAR, JUST LIKE A MERMAID
THAT WALKED OUT OF THE OCEAN,
WHICH HAD ME A LITTLE NERVOUS
BECAUSE SHE'S WAY TOO CALM AND
COLLECTED FOR SOMEONE JUST VOTED
OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO GET THIRSTY REAL
QUICK.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
>> FIRE AND SHELTER?
>> LET'S FIGURE OUT WHERE THE
FIRE IS GOING TO GO.
>> SHE EITHER ALREADY HAS AN
IMMUNITY IDOL OR SHE HAS A CLUE.
SO I BETTEROB MY BEST BEHAVIOR
BECAUSE SHE CAN BE THE HOT GIRL
WITH A GRUDGE.
>> YOU DIDN'T TAKE IT IT
PERSONALLY, I HOPE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
I'M JUST HAVE TO PROVE YOU
WRONG.
>> GOOD.
>> MORGAN WAS ABLE TO PROVIDE
FOR US, YOU KNOW, SOME GOOD
THINGS.
I KIND OF FELT THAT BOOSTED HER
CONFIDENCE A LITTLE BIT.
BUT I'M NO DUMMY.
I KNOW A SCORPD WOMAN WHEN I SEE
HER.
SHE WAS THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
FOR ME TO USE MY PURPLE PANTS
AND KIND OF, LIKE, MY
PERSONALITY TO KIND OF GET IN
WITH HER.
I WOULDN'T HAVE VOTED YOU OUT,
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
>> HE'S OLD, SO.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> FOR SURE.
ME AND BRICE KIND OF MADE A
LITTLE CONNECTION, SO FOR RIGHT
NOW, WE'RE STICKING TOGETHER.
HE'S GOT MY BACK.
I'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> PEOPLE DON'T EXPECT ANYTHING
FROM US BECAUSE THEY LABELED US
THE BEAUTIES.
THEY THINK IT'S JUST A TRIBE
FULL OF PRINCESSES AND GUYS WHO
ARE, LIKE, PRETTY BOYS WHO DON'T
REALLY WANT TO GET DIRTY.
>> GO, BOYS, GO.
YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
WE'VE GOT A COCONUT WAITING!
>> KEEP BLOWING, BABY?
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> COME ON, BABY.
>> HEAVENLY FATHER, PLEASE HELP
US GET THIS FIRE.
>> OH!
YES!
>> FIRE!
>> WE'RE GOOD, BUDDY.
>> I WAS SO EXCITED.
WE GOT FIRE RIGHT AWAY, YOU
KNOW, WITHOUT FLINT, WHICH IS
VERY HARD TO DO.
SO I'M LOVING OUR TRIBE.
YOU GUYS ARE TH THE BOMB.
>> THERE'S NOTHING IN THEIR
MINDS THAT WANTS TO CONNECT THE
BEAUTY TRIBE WITH SUCCESS BUT
IT'S HAPPENING.
WE CAN KICK BUTT OUT HERE, AND
WE'RE DOING IT.
>> IT'S OKAY!
IT'S OKAY!
I KNOW YOU HAD TO MAKE A
DECISION ON A QUICK NOTE.
I GET THAT.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
PLEASE, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> BECAUSE I WAS ALREADY SEEN AS
BEING THE WEAKEST, I FELT LIKE
THAT'S WHAT THEY WERE THEY WERE
GOING TO COME TO CAMP THINKING
THAT THIS OILEDDER, SKINNY WOMAN
WE ELIMINATED IS WEAK, SO I HAD
TO GET MYSELF RIGHT BACK ON TO
EQUAL TERMS WITH ALL OF THEM.
I ACTUALLY HAD THE OPPORTUNITY
TO GO AND LOOK FOR THE IDOL BUT
I WENT FOR THE GROUP AND GET THE
EXTRA BAG OF RICE.
>> I KNEW YOU WOULD.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> AS SOON AS WE ARRIVED TO
CAMP, TRISH CAME WITH OPEN ARMS.
SHE SAID I HAD THE CHOICE OF
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL FOR MYSELF
OR GETTING A SECOND BAG OF RICE.
IF I WAS IN TRISH'S SHOES THERE
WOULD HAVE BEEN ONLY ONE BAG OF
RICE AND ONE IDOL IN MY POCKET.
WHO WANTS TO TALK BUILDING
SHELTER?
LET'S SPLIT UP.
CHOOSE DIFFERENT CHORES.
>> LOOKING THROUGH ALL OF MY
TEAM MEMBERS, I COULD TELL ANY
THAT ANY CHALLENGE THAT WILL
HAVE PHYSICAL STRENGTH IN IT
WE'RE DEFINITELY GOING TO
DOMINATE.
WE HAVE THE BIGGEST MAN OUT
HERE.
HE'S, LIKE, EIGHT FEET TALL.
>> I PLAYED A LITTLE BASKETBALL.
>> ME BEING A BASKETBALL
ENTHUSIAST, I IMMEDIATELY KNEW
WHO THAT WAS, CLIFF ROBINSON,
PORTLAND TRAILBLAZERS, ONE OF MY
FAVORITE PLAYERS GROWING UP, AND
EVERYONE SEEMED STOKED TO HAVE
HIM ON OUR TRIBE BUT I DON'T
THINK ANYONE'S MAKING A REALLY
BIG DEAL ABOUT IT.
>> WHO DID YOU PLAY FOR?
>> I PLAYED FOR THE PORTLAND
TRAILBLAZERS.
>> COOL!
>> THE PHOENIX SUN.
THE DETROIT PISTONS.
THE FACT THAT I'M A FORMER
BASKETBALL PLAYER COULD HURST
ME, BUT TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE THEY REALLY
HAVE ANY INTEREST IN BASKETBALL,
SO FOR ME, THAT'S JUST FINE.
I CAN PLAY THIS GAME, NOT WORRY
ABOUT MY TRIBEMATES JUDGING ME
FOR WHAT I DID, AND THEY'RE JUST
LOOKING AT ME AS CLIFF ROBINSON,
ONE OF THE TRIBEMEMBERS OF
"SUR"SURVIVOR."
>> YOU TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT ME
TO DO.
>> WHEN I GET DONE, I WILL HAVE
NO OXYGEN LEFT SO YOU'LL HAVE TO
BLOW ON IT FOR A WHILE.
>> I'VE BEEN A COP FOR A WHILE
AND THERE IS A LOOK COPS HAVE
AND TONES LOOKS LIKE ONE.
WILL YOU LOOK AT ME REAL QUICK
AND BE HONEST WITH ME?
ARE YOU A COP?
>> NO.
>> YOU SWEAR?
>> I SWEAR, WHY?
I WOULDN'T HIDE THAT.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> CONSTRUCTION.
THAT'S MY MAIN THING, BUT I DO
ROOF, TOO.
>> JERSEY CITY.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE A COP.
>> I HAVE A TATTOO HERE.
THEY DON'T ALLOW THAT.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> I HAVE PLENTY OF COP FRIENDS.
YOU DON'T KNOW NO COPS?
>> I DO.
>> I HAVE MAYBE 50 FRIENDS WHO
ARE COPS.
I THOUGHT FAIR SECOND SHOULD I
TELL THEM I'M A COP.
AND I THOUGHT IF I TELL THEM I'M
A POLICE OFFICER THEY'LL BE
THINKING THIS GUY IS STRATEGIC,
TACTICAL, AND SHARP ON HIS TOES
AND THEY'LL BE RIGHT SO
OBVIOUSLY I WILL BE A THREAT TO
THEM SO THEY'LL PROBABLY TRY TO
BLINDSIDE ME.
WHAT DO YOU DO, SARAH?
>> I'M A QOP.
>> ARE YOU REALLY?
>> INTERROGATION IS PART OF MY
DAILY DUTIES AND I GET LIED TO
EVERY DAY AT WORK AND THERE'S
SOMETHING THAT MAKES ME FEEL
UNEASY ABOUT TONY.
>> YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU THE
TRUTH.
I'M NOT A.
>> YOU'RE LYING TO ME.
JUST TELL ME YOU'RE A COP.
>> COME ON!
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL HE
DOES.
ALL I KNOW IS I DON'T THINK I
CAN TRUST HIM, SO HE'S GOT TO GO
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
THAT'S ALL I'VE GOT TO SAY.
>> WHAT SUP, GUYS?
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> GET A LITTLE GROUP HUG HERE
GOING.
>> HAD IT NAILED, MAN.
>> WHEN DAVID CAME OUT AND SAID
HE WAS GOING TO PICK GARRET, I
THOUGHT YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE PICKING THE ONE GUY WHO
CAN HELP US IN CHALLENGES AND
YOU'RE OSTRACIZING HIM ALREADY.
IT'S A TERRIBLE MOVE.
>> DID YOU HAVE TO MAKE A
DECISION?
>> YEAH, I'VE GOT A COUPLE OF
THINGS ACCOMPLISHED.
I FOUND STILL WATER, AND I,
LIKE, BALLED IT ALL THE WAY TO
THE WATER FALL.
>> GOOD.
>> THERE'S A WATERFALL, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH.
>> SHUT UP.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO SIT HERE AND
PRETEND LIKE I'M SOME ARCHITECT
SO I HAVE NO IDEA HOW TO BUILD A
SHELTER.
>> I'M A NUCLEAR ENGINEER.
>> WOW.
>> I HAVE AN IDEA FOR A SHELTER.
>> YOU DO.
>> I'VE GOT A PLAN.
>> AWESOME.
>> THERE WE GO!
>> I HAVE MY Ph.D. IN NUCLEAR
ENGINEERING SO I THINK I'M THE
SMARTEST PERSON HERE, HANDS
DOWN.
I'M GOING TO BUILD THAT SHELTER.
I'M NOT GOING TO CUT THE BAMBOO
BUT I'M GOING TO TELL THEM HOW
TO BUILD IT AND IT'S GOING TO BE
AN AWESOME SHELTER.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE FOUR STAKES
ABOUT THREE FEET HIGH.
I WANT YOU TO CUT, LIKE, EIGHT
BAMBOO.
THAT'S THE FIRST THING I NEED,
THE BASE.
.
>> NICE.
>> GARRET, WHACK THAT THING.
GET THE NEXT ONE RIGHT HERE.
WE NEED TO FIND ANOTHER ONE THAT
IS THIS HEIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> SHE TOOK THE LEADERSHIP ROLE
AND HER APPROACH IS NOT THE
SLEEKEST, AND SHE DOES COME OFF
REALLY CONFRONTATIONAL AND
BOSSY.
>> YOU GO GET BAMBOO.
THAT ONE LOOKS A LITTLE TALL.
WHY DON'T YOU DO ONE OF THE
SHORTER ONES.
NO, NO, NO FLAT BACK, YUP, LIKE
THAT.
OKAY, MAKE LIKE A PALM FROND OR
SOME STACKS OF ROCKS.
ALL WE HAVE LEFT IS LONG PIECES.
>> RIGHT NOW WE HAVE AN ENGINEER
J'TIA WHO SAYS SHE CAN BUILD A
SHELTER.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
DIG THERE AND DIGGING SEEMS LIKE
THE BIGGEST FACTOR.
>> WHY DON'T WE MOVE THAT OVER
THERE?
>> SHE HAS DECISIVENESS OF A
LEADER.
SHE HAS THE BOSSINESS FOR SURE,
BUT SHE DOESN'T EXACTLY HAVE IT
ALL HERE.
>> THIS AIN'T GOING TO HOLD US
UP ANYWAY.
LOOK, IT'S--
>>AL OUR WEIGHT.
>> WE HAVE, LIKE, 500 POUNDS.
>> YEAH, WE DO, BUT BAMBOO IS
STRONG, AND IT'S THE WHOLE
STRUCTURE PART OF IT.
ALL RIGHT, I NEED SPLIT BAMBOO.
>> J'TIA I DON'T APPRECIATE HER
ATTITUDE.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY DOES.
MAKES HER UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> SHE'S QUITE BOSSY.
>> VERY BOSSY.
>> BUT SHE DOESN'T WANT TO DO
ANYTHING.
>> YEAH, SO I WOULD JUST LET HER
DO WHAT SHE DOES, YOU KNOW?
>> THAT'S MY PLAN.
>> J'TIA'S TAKEN CHARGE OF DOING
STUFF BUT SHE DOESN'T DO
ANYTHING.
SHE JUST SORT OF BARKS ORDERS TO
US.
IN MY CAREER, I HAVE ENOUGH
EXPERIENCE WITH PEOPLE WHO LOOK
LIKE THEY CAN GET THINGS DONE
BUT YOU PUT THEM AT THE PLATE,
PUT A BAT IF THEIR HAND, AND ALL
OF A SUDDEN THEY LOOK LIKE BUGS
BONE, AND THAT'S J'TIA.
>> THIS IS NOT GOING TO TAKE
LONG.
LET'S JUST GO AHEAD AND POWER IT
OUT.
WE NEED TO DO IT, LET'S JUST DO
THIS.
GOT TO DO THIS.
>> J'TIA IS JUST TOO MUCH.
SHE'S TOO MUCH.
>> LET ME CHECK THE BALANCE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> NOT VERY SMART FOR THE BRAIN
TRIBE.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING TO
MANEUVER A CART THROUGH AN
OBSTACLE COURSE.
AT EACH TOWER, YOU'LL RETRIEVE A
KEY, TIEWZ TO UPLOCK A CHEST,
PUT THE CHEST ON THE CART, AND
CONTINUE ON.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL THREE
CHESTS, YOU MUST DISASSEMBLE
YOUR CART, SLIDE IT THROUGH A
BARRICADE, PUT IT BACK TOGETHER
AND GET TO THE FINISH WHERE TWO
PEOPLE WILL USE THE PIECES
INSIDE THE CHEST TO SOLVE A
GIANT DRAGON PUZZLE.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY!
>> Jeff: IMMUNITY.
( APPLAUSE )
THIS IS WHAT YOU COVET IN THIS
GAME.
IF YOU HAVE IMMUNITY, YOU CANNOT
BE VOTED OUT.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, ARE SAFE FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE THE
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN."
THAT IS A DISTINCTION NOBODY
WANTS.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH,
FIRE-MAKING KIT.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE FIRE, THIS
WILL ENSURE YOU GET IT.
YOU CAN'T GET FIRE WITH THIS,
IT'S ON YOU.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH ALSO GETS
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
A LITTLE MORE DIFFICULT, BUT
THIS WILL GET YOU THERE.
LOSERS, NOTHING.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD IN THE
FORM OF FIRE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GET THAT BARREL OUT.
>> Jeff: FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE PEOPLE WANT TO SHOW
THE OTHER TRIBES WHAT'S GOING
ON.
SPENCER UP FOR THE BRAIN TRIBE.
BRICE HAS THE KEY FOR THE BEAUTY
TRIBE.
CLIFF HAS IT FOR THE BRAWN.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> Jeff: SPENCER HAS IT FOR
THE BRAINS.
ONCE YOU HAVE YOUR KEY, UNLOCK
THAT CHEST.
GET IT ON YOUR CART, GET TO
MOVING.
>> THE CHAIN, THE CHAIN!
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE WORKING
TOO QUICKLY, GETTING CAUGHT UP
IN THE CHAINS.
ALL THREE TRIBES HAVE THEIR
FIRST CHEST, MOVING ON TO THE
SECOND CHEST.
>> GET THAT OUT OF THE WAY.
COME BACK HERE.
COME BACK.
>> DON'T WORRY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: CLIFF HAS THE SECOND
RIPPING FOR THE BRAWN TRIBE.
BRICE HAS THE SECOND KEY FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
SPENCER HAS THE SECOND KEY FOR
THE BRAIN TRIBE.
J'TIA WORKING ON THE LOCK.
CLIFF HAS THE THIRD KEY FOR THE
BRAWN TRIBE.
BRAWN WITH A BIG LEAD RIGHT NOW.
>> UNCOTHE CHAIN.
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE CAUGHT IN
THE CHAINS AGAIN.
BEAUTY TRIBE HAS THEIR SECOND
CHEST.
BRAIN TRIBE HAS THEIR SECOND
BRAWN TRIBE HAS THEIR THIRD
CHEST.
THEY ARE STARTING TO TAKE THEIR
CART APART.
BEAUTY TRIBE HAS THEIR THIRD
KEY.
>> GO, GO.
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE HAS THEIR
THIRD KEY.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO GET THE CART
THROUGH THE OBSTACLE, AND THE
PEOPLE GO OVER.
OVER.
>> TACK IT APART!
TAKE IT APART.
>> Jeff: BEAUTIES NOW TAKING
THEIR CART APART.
BRAINS NOW TAKING THEIR PART
APART.
>> SOMEBODY HELP ME!
LET'S GO!
OVER!
>> Jeff: BRAWN TRIBE WORKING
TOGETHER VERY WELL.
THRAEF GOT THEIR CART THROUGH,
NOW JUST WORKING ON THE CHEST.
THE BEAUTY TRIBE WORKING
TOGETHER WELL.
IN LAST PLACE IS THE BRAIN
TRIBE, THE SMART GROUP, TAKING
THE LONGEST TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
GOT TO GET EVERYTHING THROUGH.
BRAWN TRIBE QUICKLY WORKING TO
GET THEIR CART BACK AFFECT.
BEAUTY TRIBE NOW DOWN TO THEIR
LAST CART.
BRAIN TRIBE STILL WITH MANY
PIECES TO GET OVER.
DISASTER FOR THE BRAIN TRIBE.
PUZZLE PIECES FALLING OUT.
BRAWN TRIBE GOING THROUGH THEIR
LAST OBSTACLE, LOGS TO GET RID
OF, ROCKS TO GET OUT OF THE WAY.
BRAIN STILL WORKING ON GETTING
THEIR CART THROUGH, FALL APART.
SMARTEST TRIBE OUT HERE AND
ANOTHER DISASTER.
PUZZLE PIECES ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
THIS IS AN ABSOLUTE FALLING
APART OF ONE TRIBE THREE DAYS
INTO CA "SURVIVOR."
WHILE THE BRAWN TRIBE IS ALREADY
WORKING ON THE PUZZLE, THE
BEAUTY TRIBE IS ABOUT TO GET
THERE, THE BRAIN TRIBE STILL
WORKING.
BRAWN TRIBE, ALREADY WELL INTO
THE PUZZLE.
THE BEAUTY TRIBE WORKING ON
THEIR PUZZLE.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE, WHATEVER
BRAINS THEY HAD HAVE CLEARLY
VMENTD 72 HOURS INTO THIS GAME.
UNBELIEVABLE HOW FAR BEHIND THEY
ARE.
BRAWN TRIBE HAS FINISHED THE
FIRST SECTION OF THEIR PUZZLE.
THEY'RE MOVING ON TO THE SECOND
SECTION.
BEAUTY TRIBE IS WORKING ON THE
SECOND SECTION.
BRAIN TRIBE MAY NOT EVEN BE ABLE
TO FINISH THIS PUZZLE, IF THEY
GET A CHANCE.
ONE OF THE WORST PERFORMANCES
OUT OF THE GATE IN THE HISTORY
OF "SURVIVOR."
THEIR CART IS FALLING APART.
>> WIRE DOING FINE, GUYS.
>> Jeff: BRAWN TRIBE DOING A
NICE JOB.
LINDSEY AND SARAH.
L.J. AND ALEXIS WORKING FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
>> NO PRESSURE, NO PRESSURE.
>> Jeff: THE BRAIN TRIBE JUST
NOW GETTING TO THE END.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: IT IS NECK AND NECK
RIGHT NOW BRAWN AND BEAUTY.
>> THERE GU!
>>
( APPLAUSE ).
>> YEAH!
>> GUYS, THIS IS GOING TO BE OUR
BEST MOMENT, LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: IF THERE WAS EVER A
TIME BRAINS NEEDED TO USE THEIR
BRAINS, IT IS RIGHT NOW IN THE
PUZZLE PORTION.
>> POUND IT A LITTLE BIT!
>> Jeff: THEY MOV NEED TO MOVE
QUICKLY.
BEAUTY TRIBE FINISHES THEIR
SECOND BOX OF PUZZLE PIECES.
THE BRAWN TRIBE HAS FINISHED
THEIR SECOND SECTIONS.
THEY'RE WORKING ON THEIR THIRD
CRATE OF PUZZLE PIECES.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT TO PICK IT
UP.
YOU'VE GOT TO START DOUBLE
TIMING IT.
IT HAS BEEN NECK AND NECK, BACK
AND FORTH, BETWEEN BRAWN AND
BEAUTY.
BEAUTY DOWN TO FOUR PIECES.
BRAWN WITH SIX PIECES.
THIS IS IT.
BEAUTY VERY CLOSE TO CLOSING
THIS FIRST CHALLENGE OUT.
BEAUTY DOWN TO TWO PIECES.
>> YOU GUYS, YOU GOT THREE
PIECES, COME ON.
>> Jeff: BRAWN VERY CLOSE TO
FINISHING.
DOWN TO ONE PIECE LEFT FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: THEY'VE DONE IT!
BEAUTY, SOLANA TRIBE, WINS
IMMUNITY, AND FIRE-MAKING KIT!
BRAWN FINISHES.
BRAWN WIBZ IMMUNITY AND FIRE IN
THE FORM THE FLINT.
BRAIN TRIBE NOWHERE CLOSE TO
FINISHING.
LUZON WILL BE THE FIRST TRIBE AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, WILL LOSE THE
FIRST TRIBEMEMBER.
SOLANA, CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
( APPLAUSE )
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
YAPAPARRI, CONGRATULATIONS, NO
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOLANA, GRAB YOUR FIRE-MAKING
KIT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
APARRI, FIRE IN THE FORM OF
FLINT.
THERE YOU GO, TONY.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> Jeff: TAKE YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
GOOD LUCK GETTING YOUR FIRE
GOING.
ALL RIGHT, LUZON, SOMEBODY FROM
YOUR GROUP WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
CAGAYAN."
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
INSTEAD OF TRYING TO GO OVER WE
SHOULD HAVE EVERYBODY PICKED
THAT UP AND WALKED.
>> WE CANNOT UNDERESTIMATE --
>> THE OTHER TRIBES.
>> WE CAN'T KEEP SAYING STUPID
STUFF LIKE, "WE'RE SO MUCH
SMARTER THAN THEM."
THEY'RE KICKING OUR ASS.
>> AT THE CHALLENGE WE SUCKED.
I CAN'T REALLY BLAME ANY
PARTICULAR PERSON.
I THINK IT'S EVERYONE, AND IT'S,
LIKE, WE'RE BOOK SMART, BUT WHEN
IT COMES TO PLAYING THIS GAME,
WE'RE DUMB.
>> WE PERFORMED EXACTLY HOW WE
HAVE BEEN PERFORMING FOR THREE
DAYS-- NO EXECUTION.
>> WE HAD NOT ASSIGNED TASKS.
>> J'TIA TOOK THE FIRST KEY.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WERE DOING
KEYS.
>> I WAS.
SHE LITERALLY GRABBED IT OUT OF
THE AIR.
>> BUT SHE DIDN'T TAKE THE
CHAINS OUT.
>> I KNOW--
>> WHATEVER.
I WANT TO MOVE PAST IT BUT WHAT
I REALLY WANT TO TALK ABOUT IS
J'TIA VERSUS GARRET.
THAT WAS A PHYSICAL CHALLENGE.
AND GARRET WAS NOT HELPING.
PERSONALLY, I'D LIKE TO GET RID
OF GARRET BECAUSE I VIEW HIM AS
A BIGGER THREAT TO ME THAN
J'TIA.
I'M THINKING ABOUT DAY 39.
AND MY BIGGEST CONCERN IS THAT
I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE WHAT PUT
HIM ON THE BRAINS TRIBE.
HE HASN'T TOLD US.
AND THAT SCARES ME REALLY TO MY
CORE.
>> JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
>> NO, J'TIA.
ALL THE WAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THIS TIME--
>> FOR HARMONY, TRIBE HARMONY.
I JUST WANT TO SAY J'TIA, SEE
YA.
WOULDN'T WANT TO BE YOU.
DAVID, HE WANTS GARRET TO GO
FIRST, BUT THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
HE'S OUR STRONGEST GUY.
PLUS HE'S A WORK HORSE.
BUT J'TIA, SHE HAS NOT BEEN
PULLING HER WEIGHT.
SHE'S BEEN DOING A LOT OF
DIRECTION, AND NO PRODUCTION.
AND EVERYONE SEES IT.
SHE'S DEAD WEIGHT.
SO LET'S JUST SEND HER HOME.
>> THIS SUCKS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WHO DO YOU WANT TO VOTE OUT?
ARE YOU GOOD AS LONG AS IT'S NOT
YOU.
>> HONESTLY, I'M LEANING TOWARDS
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN PULL YOUR
WEIGHT AROUND CAMP.
YOU TELL US A LOT WHAT TO DO,
BUT I DON'T SEE YOU, YOU KNOW,
DOING ANYTHING.
>> I THINK I MORE THAN PULLED MY
WEIGHT IN THE CHALLENGE, THOUGH.
>> WELL, YOU'VE BEEN RESTING FOR
THREE DAYS.
I MEAN, YOU--
>> ARE YOU MORE THAN WELCOME TO
YOUR OPINION.
>> RIGHT.
>> I GET IT.
>> I MEAN, I'M AN HONEST PERSON.
>> I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> THAT'S HOW I AM.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> SO IT'S TIME TO SCRAMBLE,
PROBABLY.
>> I WENT UP TO KASS, AND SHE
WAS VERY HONEST.
SHE SAID SHE DOESN'T THINK I
WORK AROUND CAMP AND THAT I'M
GOING HOME.
KASS KIND OF HURT MY FEELINGS A
LITTLE BIT.
I'M NOT LAZY.
WE NEED A SHELTER, AND IF I
DIDN'T LIGHT A FIRE UNDER THE
TRIBE'S BUTT WE WOULDN'T HAVE
GOT IT DONE.
I FELT LIKE I WAS BEING
MOTIVATING.
CLEARLY IT, DOESN'T COME OFF
THAT WAY.
I JUST HOPE I HAVE NOT RUINED BY
CHANCES.
I MIGHT HAVE.
>> WHAT'S UP, GIRL?
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M PRETTY MUCH
TOAST.
I JUST TALKED TO KASS.
AND SHE'S LEANING TOWARDS VOTING
ME OUT.
>> SHE TOLD YOU THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE I'M NOT
DOING ENOUGH AROUND CAMP?
>> HONESTLY, THERE WAS ONE TIME
YOU WERE SITTING DOWN AND YOU'RE
LIKE, "MOVE THAT OVER THERE.
MOVE THAT OVER THERE."
AND I THINK IT MAY HAVE RUBBED
SOME PRIME THE WRONG WAY.
>> YOU GUYS OKAY?
>> YEAH, COME SIT.
>> I'M FEELING A LITTLE
APPREHENSIVE.
>> BUT THE THING IS, YOU'RE
ALWAYS SCARED, YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M SCARED.
BUT AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU'RE FINE.
LOOK AT ME.
I'M NOT LYING TO YOU.
IF YOU ASK ME, DAVID IS A
STRATEGIC THREAT TO ALL OF US,
BUT WE VOTE TOGETHER.
DAVID'S GOING TO GO HOME, AND
WE'RE ALL GOING TO FEEL BETTER,
OKAY.
J'TIA IS DEFINITELY PRETTY
PARANOID RIGHT NOW, AND FOR WHAT
IT'S WORTH SHE HAS A PRETTY GOOD
REASON.
SHE'S BOSSY.
SHE DOESN'T GET ALONG WITH
EVERYONE.
I PERSONALLY CARE LESS ABOUT
THAT THAN OTHERS BECAUSE AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED, THE BIGGEST
THREAT IS DAVID.
HE'S VERY INTELLIGENT.
I DO THINK HE'S A SCHEMER, AND
HE'S ALREADY MADE IT CLEAR THAT
HE WANTS TO GET RID OF ME, SO
DAVID'S GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> I MAY BE BOSSY, BUT I AM
LOYAL.
>> YOU AND ME, WE'RE GOOD.
TASHUYOU AND J'TIA GOOD.
I'M GOING TO TALK TO SPENCER, SO
EVERYTHING'S GOOD.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT I'M
ABSOLUTELY SET ON, BUT I THINK
WE SHOULD JUST PUT FOUR VOTES ON
DAVID.
>> WELL, WHAT I'M CONCERNED
ABOUT IS YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
ANYTHING ABOUT, LIKE, IDOL CLUES
OR ANYTHING HAVE YOU?
>> NOTHING.
>> WELL, IT JUST SEEMS WEIRD
THAT THERE HASN'T BEEN ANYTHING
TO DO WITH AN IDOL SO FAR.
I WOULD THINK THERE WOULD BE A
CLUE SOMEWHERE.
I JUST THINK THAT WOULD BE,
LIKE, A DAVID IF DAVID FOUND IT.
>> YEAH.
HAVE YOU NOTICED THAT WITH HIM,
LIKE SNEAKING OFF OR ANYTHING
LIKE THAT?
>> I MEAN, THEY BOTH WENT OFF
TOGETHER ALONE, AND HE'S PRETTY
SHIFTY, AND I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
HE HAS IN HIS BACK POCKET, SO
HELP.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'M REALLY CONCERNED ABOUT
VOTING OUT DAVID.
I KNOW IN THE PAST THERE HAVE
BEEN CLUES AND IDOLS AROUND
CAMP.
>> AND KEEP SEEING DAVID AND
KASS WALK OFF AND JUST WARNED
AROUND.
SO I'M A BIT WORRIED THAT HE
COULD HAVE FOUND IT.
SO I'M THINKING SINCE J'TIA IS A
PAIN IN THE ASS, LET'S VOTE HER
OUT, JUST TO BE SAFE.
IT JUST SEEMS LIKE A RISK WE
TONIGHT NEED TO TAKE BECAUSE
THAT WOULD SUCK IF THEY PLAYED
AN IDOL AND ONE OF US WERE OUT.
>> SPENCER IS PARANOID ABOUT
DAVID HAVING THE IDOL WHICH IS
RIDICULOUS BECAUSE I HAVE THE
IDOL.
OF COURSE I'M NOT GOING TO TELL
HIM THAT, BUT NOW I FEEL NERVOUS
ABOUT VOTING FOR DAVID BECAUSE
IT LOOKS LIKE I DON'T HAVE FOUR
SOLID VOTES FOR TONIGHT.
>> THE RAIN'S COMING, GUYS.
>> YEAH.
>> WITHOUT QUESTION, DAVID IS
JUST A HUGE THREAT.
AND IF PEOPLE DON'T SEE THAT,
THEY'RE IDIOTS.
I DON'T KNOW.
I HOPE THAT SPENCER AND I STAY
STRONG TOGETHER BUT WE'LL SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
( THUNDER )
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH,
APPROACH THE FLAME, DIP IT IN
AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART RITUAL OF TRIBAL
COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS GAME,
FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
AND WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO
ARE YOU.
THAT'S GOING TO BE THE CASE FOR
ONE OF YOU TONIGHT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> LIKE A BIG SPIDER.
IT'S FINE.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE TELLING ME ALL
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH THESE THREE
DAYS A SPIDER?
>> IT'S, LIKE, CRAWL ON ME.
>> Jeff: SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
THE FIRST FEW DAYS.
J'TIA, YOU'RE ALREADY SMILING.
>> OH, I KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO
WANT TO TALK TO ME A LOT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: WHY DO YOU THINK I'M
GOING TOMENT TO TALK TO YOU A
LOT?
>> BECAUSE SOME PEOPLE ARE
CONSIDERING ME FOR THE VOTE
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: AND HERE WE ARE OFF
AND RUNNING.
SO YOU THINK YOU'RE IN TROUBLE
TONIGHT.
>> OH, YEAH, KASS TOLD ME SHE
WAS THINKING ABOUT ME.
SHE TOLD ME I WASN'T HISPANIC
AROUND CAMP.
I DIDN'T KNOW I CAME ACROSS LIKE
THAT.
I'M AN ENGINEER, I CAME OUT.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO HIT IT.
I HAD A BIG PLAN FOR THE
SHELTER, JEFF, I GAVE UP ON THE
INSTRUCTIONS.
THAT'S BOSSY AS HELL.
I GET IT.
NOBODY LIKES TO BE BOSSED
AROUND, AND THE SHELTER,
LITERALLY, IT FELL ON ITS SIDE.
>> Jeff: DAVID WHAT, HAS BEEN
IT LIKE FOR YOU REGARDING J'TIA?
>> SHE CAME OUT VERY STRONG.
SHE SAID SHE WAS A NUCLEAR
PHYSICIST OR NUCLEAR BOMB
BUILDER OR SOMETHING THAT MADE
ME FEEL LIKE, WOW, LET'S LISTEN
TO HER.
AND IT WAS GOING WELL UNTIL IT
WASN'T GOING WELL ANYMORE.
>> Jeff: YES, YTEA.
>> I'M A NUCLEAR ENGINEER--
THANKS, DAVID-- I NEVER SAID I
BUILT A SHELTER BEFORE AND I HAD
A PLAN AND I WAS VERY EXCITED
ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: J'TIA A MOMENT AGO
YOU WERE THE ONE SAYING I KIND
OF BLEW IT.
THE MINUTE DAVID CONFIRMS THAT
YOU SAID HANG ON.
>> NO, MY PLAN DIDN'T WORK.
I'M BUMMED ABOUT THAT.
I'M DOING WHAT I CAN.
I THINK I'M A RELATIONSHIP
PERSON, IF I'M TALKING TOO MUCH,
TELL ME TO SHUT UP.
I'M ALWAYS OPEN TO SUGGESTION.
I WANT US TO SICK SEED AS A
TRIBE.
>> Jeff: LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
EARLY MOMENTS RIGHT OUT OF THE
GATE.
DAVID UHAVE TO CHOOSE THE
WEAKEST PERSON ON THIS TRIBE AND
INSTANTLY YOU PICK GARRET.
>> I REALIZED THAT IT WAS NOT
THE PERFECT POSITION TO BE IN
AND I DECIDED TO ACT WITH HASTE
AND NOT DITHER AROUND AND THAT'S
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
YOU HAVE TO STEP UP BECAUSE,
LISTEN.
THIS IS A GAME.
>> Jeff: SO, GARRET, HOW DID
IT FEEL FOR YOU TO BE ONE OF THE
STRONGEST GUYS OUT HERE, AND
DAVID, WITHOUT HESITATING GOES,
"GARRET, HE'S OUR WEAKEST?"
>> SUCTION.
IT IS NEVER FUN TO BE CAST AS
THE OUTSIDER.
THAT HAPPENING THREE MINUTES IN
WAS NO FUN.
>> Jeff: IS THERE ANY PART OF
YOU,ING MAYBE I'M A STANDING
TARGET AND I'M OUT OF THIS GAME?
>> NO.
I TRUST MY TEAM.
>> Jeff: DAVID, IS GARRET OKAY
IN HIS CONFIDENCE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: HE'S NOT GOING
ANYWHERE?
>> NOT TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: SO, J'TIA, NOW AS WE
GET CLOSER TO THE VOTE.
WHAT IF IT'S YOU?
YOU'RE THE FIRST OUT.
>> IT WOULD SUCK.
I CAME OUT HERE TO PLAY AND I
FEEL LIKE IF YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT GETTING FURTHER AS THE
TRIBE, YOU CAN'T THINK ABOUT THE
LAST TWO-THIRD.
YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT THE
FIRST THIRD AND GETTING THERE.
>> Jeff:LET LAST TWO-THIRD
COMMENT IS GOING BACK TO
SOMETHING DAVID SAID AT THE VERY
BEGINNING OF THE GAME WHEN HE
SAID,"I'M ALREADY LOOKING DOWN
TO THE END."
>> YES, SO, THIS IS MY TRIBE.
THESE ARE MY PEOPLE AND SOMEBODY
GOT TO GO.
I GET THAT.
>> Jeff: BUT YOU DON'T AT THE
PRESENT TIME TO BE YOU.
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
NOT AT ALL.
>> Jeff: THEN WHO?
>> DAVID.
>> Jeff: DAVID, SHE THREW IT
RIGHT AT YOU.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, THAT'S WHEN
YOU'RE GOING TO BE VOTED OUT,
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
I MEAN, IT'S-- IF YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO BE VOTED OUT, I
SHOULD SAY.
>> Jeff: SO, SPENCER, CLEARLY,
BIG VOTE.
( THUNDER )
( LAUGHTER )
THE "SURVIVOR" GOD ARE SPEAKING.
SPENCER.
>> YEAH, IT'S ALL ABOUT
ESTABLISHING HOW THE TRIBE IS
GOING TO GO FORWARD SO WE HAVE
TO GO INTO IT THINKING WHO DO WE
VOTE OUT SO OUR TRIBE'S GOING TO
GET ALONG?
IT'S TOUGH, BUT AT THE END OF
THE DAY, YOU HAVE TO KIND OF GO
WITH THE PEOPLE YOU TRUST.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
KASS, YOU'RE UP.
>> IN THE REAL WORLD, I MAY HIRE
YOU.
BUT IN THIS WORLD, NOT TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULDN'T TIME TO DO
SO.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ, THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
( THUNDER )
>> Jeff: ONCE THE VOTES ARE
READ THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, J'TIA.
DAVID.
J'TIA.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES J'TIA, TWO VOTES
DAVID.
THERE'S THREE VOTES DAVID.
TWO VOTES J'TIA, ONE VOTE LEFT.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN," DAVID.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DAVID, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, HOPEFULLY TONIGHT'S VOTE
WILL POINT THIS TRIBE IN THE
DIRECTION IT NEEDS TO GO BECAUSE
YOU'VE GOT TO GET IT TOGETHER
QUICKLY, AND I DON'T JUST MEAN
SHELTER.
GOOD NEWS ABOUT TRIBAL.
YOU DO GET FIRE IN THE FORM OF
FLINT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> I HAVE NO REGRETS.
I PLAYED THE WAY I THOUGHT I
NEED TO PLAY TO GET FORWARD IN
THE GAME.
AND THE TRIBE JUST DOESN'T HAVE
IT TOGETHER.
OR THEY HAVE IT TOGETHER JUST
AGAINST ME.
BUT NO HARD FEELINGS TO ANY OF
THEM.
I CONSIDER MYSELF PRETTY MUCH
THE LUCKIEST PERSON IN THE
WORLD.
>> ANYBODY GOT ANY SUGGESTIONS
ABOUT THIS FIRE?
LET'S GET THE PARTY STARTED.
>> LAST NIGHT, TRIBAL WAS A LOT
OF RANDOM ARGUING, BUT, YOU
KNOW, IN THE END, THE REAL POINT
OF TRIBAL WAS TO SEND DAVID HOME
AND WE WERE ABLE TO SUCCESSFULLY
DO THAT.
BUT I'M NOT HAVING FUN PLAYING
"SURVIVOR."
THIS ISN'T FUN FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO BE HONEST.
MANUAL LABOR ISN'T FUN.
STARVING ISN'T FUN.
LIKE, IT'S NOT LIKE A COOL
ADVENTURE FOR ME.
>> JUST REMEMBER, IT'S ALL ABOUT
OXYGEN, SO WHEN YOU BUILD IT,
MAKE SURE TO GET THE AIR FLOW.
>> SEPARATE IT A LITTLE BIT.
>> YES.
>> WHEN I'M PLAYING POKER I'M
SIT NAIG COMFORTABLE CHAIR.
CHICK EXPEP VEGETABLES ARE BEING
BROUGHT TO ME RIGHT AT THE
TABLE.
I WANT TO PLAY "SURVIVOR" TO
OUTPLAY AND OUTWIT PEOPLE.
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY "SURVIVOR"
TO SURVIVE IN THE WILDERNESS.
LET'S SAY WE HAVE TRIBAL AGAIN
TONIGHT.
WE GO WITH KASS RIGHT NOW.
AND WE VOTE OFF ONE OF THE TWO
GIRLS, RIGHT?
>> TRIBAL WENT PERFECT.
>> RIGHT.
>> BECAUSE SHE WAS FIGHTING WITH
TASHA.
SHE ALREADY DOESN'T LIKE J'TIA.
SO TRIBAL I THINK MADE US IN A
BETTER POSITION.
>> KASS WAS DEFINITELY
BLINDSIDED BY DAVID GOING HOME
LAST NIGHT.
SPENCER AND I ARE SETTING
OURSELVES UP IF WE DO HAVE TO
VOTE SOMEONE OFF WE HAVE
OPTIONS.
J'TIA AND TASHA.
BUT ALSO IF I FEEL LIKE WE CAN'T
REALLY TRUST KASS, MAYBE WE JUST
TAKE HER OUT.
YOU KNOW, I JUST LIKE WORKING
WITH THE TWO OF YOU MORE, YOU
KNOW, FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
>> YEAH.
>> TRIBAL WAS INTERESTING.
A LITTLE BLINDSIDE OF DAVID AND
ME.
BUT ALL I THOUGHT WAS I'M NUMBER
THREE FOR SOMEONE, AND THEY KNOW
IT.
>> I THINK WE SEE THAT IT MAKES
SENSE FOR YOU TO BE WITH US AND
IT DEFINITELY MAKES SENSE FOR US
TO BE WITH YOU.
>> THE BOYS AREN'T GOINGS TO
BREAK UP AND THE GIRLS AREN'T
GOING TO BREAK UP.
SO WHERE DOES THAT LEAF ME?
SWING VOTE.
>> I MEAN, FOR EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENED IN THE PAST, WE HAVE A
SOLID FINAL THREE PACT RIGHT
NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> AND WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
>> I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
I TALKED TO GARRETT AND SPENCER,
BUT I'M NOT 100% WITH THEM.
AND I'M GOING TO WORK WHATEVER
ANGLE.
I HAVE NO ALLEGIANCE RIGHT NOW.
>> SHAKE ON IT?
FINAL THREE.
>> WE CAN DO OUR STUPID HANDED
SHAKE.
I DON'T CARE.
IT'S GAME ON, AS LONG AS IT'S
NOT ME.
>> GO GET THEM, FAELS.
>> ALL RIGHT, WOO.
>> ME AND WOO WE COOPERATE WAIT
TO TAKE THAT BOAT OUT.
WE HAVE BEEN LOOKING AT THAT
BOAT FOR A FEW DAYS NOW.
JUST ITCHING AT THE BIT TO GO
OUT THERE AND TRY TO DO SOME
FISHING.
>> LOOK AT THESE GUYS.
THEY LOOK LIKE REAL ISLANDERS
OUT THERE, DON'T THEY.
>> WE'LL SEE WHAT THEY COME BACK
WITH.
>> HOW DO-- HOW DO WE TURN
AGAIN?
>> LEFT TO GO RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO DOCK IT OVER THERE?
>> YEAH, LET'S GO SEE WHAT'S
OVER THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I LIKE WOO.
AND YOU GOTTA HAVE A WING BAN.
BATMAN ALREADY HAD ROBIN.
JORDAN HAD PIPPIN.
CLIFF HAS WOO.
WOO TANG.
SO, YOU KNOW, YOU JUST GOTTA
TAKE YOUR WING MAN AND DO WHAT
YOU GOTTA DO TO TAKE CARE OF
BUSINESS.
>> UH-OH!
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
( LAUGHING )
>> EVERYTHING WAS GOING WELL,
BUT WE LOST THE-- WE LOST THE
BALANCE ON THE BOAT, AND ALL OF
A SUDDEN --
>> WILL YOU DO ME A FAVOR, HELP
ME TIP THIS?
IT CAPSIZED, WE GOT A LITTLE
WATER IN IT.
>> HOW YOU FLIPPING THIS?
>> I FIGURE MIGHT AS WELL TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THE BRAWN THAT'S ON
THE BEACH AND DO WHAT WE CAN TO
TIP THE WATER OUT.
>> IT'S COMING OUT, GUYS.
>> HOW IS THAT?
GOOD.
>> NO, THERE'S STILL A BUNCH IN
THERE.
JUST HOLD IT FOR A MINUTE.
>> CLIFF IS A VERY LIKABLE GUY.
HE'S FUNNY.
HE HAS A LOT OF CHARISMA, AND I
WOULD SAY HE'S PROBABLY THE MOST
LIKED ON OUR TRIBE RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, YOU DON'T NEED TO GO
HIGHER.
JUST HOLD IT.
>> I'M LOOKING AT CLIFF, I CAN'T
TELL YOU FOR A FACT WHAT
BASKETBALL TEAM HE WAS ON OR
WHAT HE DID FOR A LIVING OR WHAT
HE DOES FOR A LIVING BECAUSE I
DON'T REALLY CARE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WERE YOU SCARED?
>> NO, IT WASN'T TOO BAD.
>> AND THEN WE HAVE LINDZY AND
SARAH AND WOO.
APPARENTLY THEY LOVE HIM.
THEY'RE, LIKE, FANS OF HIM.
>> I HONESTLY LOVE CLIFF.
I THINK HE'S FANTASTIC.
I REALLY DO.
>> THIS IS A GAME.
I UNDERSTAND HOW THE GAME IS
PLAYED.
I'VE JUST GOT TO MAKE SURE I'M
AWARE OF WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> OUR FIRST MISSION-- FAIL.
>> TODAY IS DEFINITELY BEAUTIFUL
ON A BEAUTIFUL TRIBE, BUT
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE PLAYING
DUMB OUT HERE, AND I'M ON TO IT.
ALEXIS IS JUST BEING THE FLIRT
OUT HERE.
JUST KIND OF, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
DEFINITELY ALL ABOUT HER
SEXUALITY AND ALWAYS IN HER
PANTIES, KIND OF LIKE, "YOU WANT
SOME COCONUT WATER?"
SO I DEFINITELY SEE HER GAME.
JEFRA, I DON'T KNOW WHAT HER
GAME IT.
>> ARE YOU ALL URINATING A LOT.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT POOPING, BUT
ARE YOU BEING?
MAYBE ONCE A DAY SO THAT CANNOT
BE GOOD FOR US.
>> ALL OF HER CRAYONS ON CRAYON
BOX ARE NOT BRIGHT.
>> YOU LOOK CUTE IN YOUR BOWLING
SOCKS.
>> I ONLY SEE HIM AS A FRIEND IN
MY EYES BUT HE MIGHT SEE ME AS
SOMETHING MORE.
SO I THINK IF I NEEDED TO, I
COULD DEFINITELY REEL HIM IN,
AND HE WOULD BE RIGHT THERE IN
MY BACK POCKET.
I'M FROM, LIKE, THE SILICON
VALLEY, SO IT'S ALL REALLY TECH
AND, LIKE, ENGINEERS.
THOSE NERD TRIBE WOULD LOVE
WHERE I LIVE.
>> JEREMIAH HAS BEEN DROOLING
OVER MORGAN AND ME BEING THE
ULTIMATE WING MAN, I CAN
FACILITATE FOR HIM TO KIND OF
GET TO WORK WITH MORGAN AND BE
AROUND THE HOT GIRL.
>> DOES JEFRA GET ON YOUR NERVES
AT ALL?
>> HECK, YEAH.
>> I JUST SIT HERE SMILING.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE NEED TO BE,
LIKE THE BRAINS, THE OPERATION.
>> YEAH.
>> UH-HUH.
>> I MEAN, IF Y'ALL WILL TRUST
ME--
>> US COUNTRY FOLK HAVE TO STICK
TOGETHER.
I THINK WHEN MY TRIBE FIRST MET
ME, THEY KIND OF THOUGHT I WOULD
BE THE FOURTH GIRL ON THE TRIBE
JUST LAYING OUT ALL DAY.
DON'T JUDGE A BOOK BY ITS COVER.
I'M PLAYING THE GAME.
>> ARE ANY OF THOSE SEMIDRY,
TRISH?
WHAT ABOUT THIS GUY?
>> THERE'S PLENTY OF WOOD TO BE
HAD IF YOU WANT TO GO GRAB SOME,
LINDSEY.
THERE'S PLENTY OF WOOD UP THERE.
>> IS THERE, LIKE, AN ISSUE?
I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE HAVING AN
ISSUE WITH ME RIGHT NOW.
>> NO, I'M JUST SAYING WE COULD
HAVE FIRE IF-- WE NEED TO HAVE
FIRE FOR THE NEXT 39 DAYS.
WE NEED AS MUCH WOOD AS WE
POSSIBLY CAN.
>> WHY IS IT ME, THOUGH?
WHY IS IT ON ME?
>> WELL, WE'RE ALL TRYING TO
CHIP IN.
>> EXACTLY.
SO WHY AM I NOT CHIPPING IN?
>> LEAVE HER ALONE.
NOW TRICIA, SHE NEEDS TO CHILL
OUT BECAUSE I CAN'T STAND HER
VOICE.
I CAN'T STAND HER ATTITUDE.
I CAN'T STAND THE FACT THAT
SHE'S SO JUDGMENTAL.
LINDSEY, I JUST WISH WE COULD
JUST CONTRIBUTE LIKE EVERYBODY
ELSE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO CONTRIBUTE.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
OH, MY GOSH.
I CANNOT STAND HER.
>> WHAT'S UP, TRISH, YOU ALL
RIGHT?
>> SHE'S JUST SITTING DOWN
THERE, KISSING CLIFF'S ASS.
>> LISTEN--
>> I THINK EVERYBODY IS STARTING
TO SEE WHAT I SEE, HOW LINDSEY
DOESN'T HELP OUT AT ALL, AND HOW
ANNOYING SHE CAN BE AROUND CAMP.
I'M FROM BOSTON, MASS.
SHE HASN'T MET ME YET.
BECAUSE IF I REALLY SNAPPED ON
HER, SHE'D STILL BE CRYING.
RIGHT NOW.
>> LINDSEY'S IN LOVE WITH CLIFF
BECAUSE OF I HAD BASKETBALL
ABILITIES AND WHATEVER IT IS,
AND I'VE GOT YOUR BACK, ALL
RIGHT.
I'M ALL YOU'VE GOT, AND YOU'RE
ALL I'VE GOT.
I TRUST TRISH.
SHE'S A GENUINE PERSON.
SHE'S OUT THERE BUSTING HER ASS,
TOO, WHILE EVERYBODY ELSE IS
FULL OF DRAMA.
YOU'RE A SWEETHEART BUT YOU HAVE
TO BE STRONG OUT HERE.
>> I'M STRONG.
>> DON'T LET THEM WEASEL THEIR
WAY IN YOUR LADY AND TELL YOU
THIS IS WHAT'S GOING ON.
IT'S NOT.
I'LL TELL YOU LATER WHAT I'M
WORK WORKING ON OVER THERE.
TRISH AND I ARE WALKING ON
EGGSHELLS WITH THESE PEOPLE AND
THAT'S WHERE I CAME UP WITH THE
IDEA OF SPYING ON THEM.
I ACT LIKE I'M TRYING TO PROTECT
THEM FROM THE RAIN AND
EVERYTHING BUT I'LLING ABOUT A
SPY SHACK.
I'M TRYING TO COVER UP A
CUBBYHOLE IN THE CORNER AND I'M
GOING TO RUN AROUND THE BEACH
AND CRAWL UP TO HERE AND LISTEN
TO WHAT THEY HAVE TO SAY AND I'M
GOING TO HEAR EVERYTHING.
SO WHATEVER USELESS CLIFF TELLS
WEASEL WOO, THAT'S CRUCIAL
INFORMATION.
THAT'S THE KEY TO THIS.
IT'S NOT JUST SMALL TALK.
IT'S GOING TO BE BIG TALK.
THAT'S WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
MY MAIN TARGET IS CLIFF, THE
LION, THE PRIDE.
IN ORDER TO TAKE OVER THE PRIDE,
THE OTHER LION HAS TO COME IN
AND KILL THAT ONE.
AND THEN HE HAS TO KILL THE
CUBS.
I HAVE MORE BRAIN THAN BRAWN.
LITTLE DO THEY KNOW.
>> BRAWNS AND BEAUTY, GETTING
YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW BRAIN
TRIBE.
DAVID VOTED OUT AT THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
I'LL TAKE BACK THE IDOLS.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, EACH
TRIBE WILL SWIMUTE TO A LARGE
BAMBOO CAGE.
YOOL CLIMB UP AND OVER THE WALL,
JUMP INTO THE WATER, WHERE YOU
WILL FIND FOUR LARGE NICHE
TRAPS.
YOU MUST THEN UNTIE THE CAGE
DOOR, PUSH THE TRAPS THROUGH,
AND BRING THEM BACK TO SHORE,
WHERE ONE TRIBE MEMBER WILL USE
THE PIECES INSIDE TO SOLVE A
VERY COMPLICATED FISH PUZZLE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN."
IN ADDITION YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH
WINS A LARGE FISH KIT,
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO GET A LOT
OF FISH.
YOU HAVE NETS.
YOU HAVE WORMS.
LURES.
AND IF YOU HAVE ANY LUCK WITH
THE FISH, A FEW THINGS TO HELP
YOU COOK IT UP-- A PAN, SOME
OIL, SOME SALT AND PEPPER.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH WINS A
SLIGHTLY SMALLER FISH REWARD.
LURES, WEIGHTS, AND FISHING
LINE.
FOR THE LOSERS, NOTHING BUT A
DATE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL WITH ME
WHERE YOU WILL VOTE SOMEBODY
OUT.
BRAWN, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
MEMBER, WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SIT
OUT?
>> ARE YOU COOL?
>> YEAH I'M COOL.
>> CLIFF.
>> Jeff: CLIFF GOING TO SIT
THIS ONE OUTS.
BEAUTY TRIBE YOU'RE SITTING
SOMEBODY OUT, WHO IS IT GOING TO
BE?
>> BRICE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CLIFF AND
BRICE, TAKE A SPOT ON THE SIT-UP
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
EVERYBODY'S SWIMMING WELL
TOGETHER.
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO GET TO THE
CAGE BEFORE YOU CAN START GOING
OVER.
J'TIA, THE SLOWEST SWIMMER OUT
HERE.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS, GOOD JOB.
>> GO, BRAWN!
GO, BEAUTY!
BRAIN TRIBE STILL WAITING ON
J'TIA.
GO, BRAIN!
>> GOT IT?
>> Jeff: BRAWN IS GOING TO BE
THE FIRST TRIBE TO GET EVERYBODY
OVER.
THEY'RE ALL IN.
GET DOWN.
START WORKING ON THAT CAGE.
BRAINS STILL STRUGGLING TO GET
OVER.
BEAUTY HAS EVERYBODY IN.
BRAIN HAS EVERYBODY IN.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO START UNTYING
KNOTS TO RELEASE THAT FRONT
GATE.
ALL THREE TRIBES WORKING
TOGETHER WELL, TAKING TURNS
GOING DOWN.
>> Jeff: BRAWN TRIBE HAS THEIR
GATE RELEASED.
BRAIN TRIBE HAS THEIR GATE
RELEASED.
NOW START SWIMMING THOSE FISH
TRAPS OUT.
THEY'RE HEAVY.
>> BEAUTY HAS THEIR CAGE DOOR
OPEN.
BRAIN WAS THE LAST TRIBE OUT,
BUT THEY HAVE PICKED UP SOME
TIME.
THIS IS AN EXHAUSTING CHALLENGE.
A LOT OF WEIGHT IN THOSE FISH
TRAPS.
IT IS NOT EASY.
BRAINS CONTINUE TO WORK WELL
TOGETHER IN THE WATER.
LED BY GARRETT.
>> LET'S GO, WE'RE WINNING!
>> Jeff: GREAT EFFORT BY THE
BRAIN TRIBE, AND A HUGE LEAD.
BRAIN TRIBE IS BACK WITH ALL
FOUR OF THEIR FISH TRAPS.
THERE YOU GO!
START UNTYING.
THE BRAWN HAS LOST A LOT OF
MOMENTUM.
>> HOOK IT UP ON MY FOOT.
>> Jeff: THE BEAUTY TRIBE HAS
NOT MADE ANY PROGRESS.
>> WHAT'S THE TRICK?
>> THERE IS NO TRICK.
>> GUYS, WE ACTUALLY HAVE A
LEAD.
>> COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
>> DO NOT GET CONFIDENT!
>> Jeff: A HUGE TIME ADVANTAGE
FOR THE BRAIN TRIBE.
BRAWN TRIBE IS NOW BACK WITH ALL
FOUR FISH TRAPS.
>> LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: THE BEAUTIES'
IPABILITY IS GIVING THE BRAWN A
CHANCE TO STAY IN THIS.
J'TIA ALREADY WORKING FOR THE
BRAIN TRIBE.
BRAWN HUSTLING TO GET THESE
PIECES OUT.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE BLEEDING.
SARAH'S FINGERS CLIPPED PRETTY
WELL.
TONY'S CUT.
>> THAT'S A BIG CHUNK OF SKIN,
MAN.
>> Jeff: THIS IS "SURVIVOR"
WELCOME TO THE GAME.
IT IS SARAH SOLVING THE PUZZLE
FOR THE BRAWN TRIBE, WHICH NOW
HAS BLOOD ALL OVER IT, AND J'TIA
SOLVING THE PUZZLE FOR THE BRAIN
TRIBE.
J'TIA STILL LOOKING FOR THAT
FIRST PIECE.
BIG ADVANTAGE RIGHT NOW FOR
BRAINS AND BRAWN BECAUSE BEAUTY
IS STILL IN THE WATER.
>> HOLD ON.
SOARA WITH THE FIRST PIECE FOR
THE BRAWN TRIBE.
J'TIA WITH HER FIRST PIECE.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: SARAH WITH HER SECOND
PIECE.
BEAUTY TRIBE STILL WORKING ON
GET THESE PUZZLE PIECES BACK.
KEEP DIGGING!
YOU ARE STILL IN THIS!
SARAH WITH HER THIRD PIECE.
J'TIA STILL STRUGGLING.
SARAH WITH HER FOURTH PIECE.
J'TIA WITH ONE.
BEAUTY TRIBE TRYING TO GET IN
THIS.
SARAH WITH HER FIFTH PIECE.
>> STAY FOCUSED.
DON'T GET-- DON'T FREAK OUT.
>> Jeff: SARAH WITH HER SIXTH
PIECE.
SHE HAS TWO PIECES LEFT.
BRAINS STILL IN TROUBLE.
J'TIA WITH JUST ONE PIECE.
SARAH WITH THE SEVENTH PIECE.
ONE PIECE LEFT FOR THE BRAWN
TRIBE.
BRAWN TRIBE WINS IMMUNITY AND
REWARD.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE
TRIBE.
YOU ARE STILL BOTH THERE THIS.
J'TIA HAS HAD A LOT OF TIME IN
THIS PUZZLE, HAS ONLY ONE PIECE
TO SHOW FOR IT.
L.J. HAS HIS FIRST PIECE FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
L.J. WITH HIS SECOND PIECE.
BEAUTY TRIBE NOW IN THE LEAD,
J'TIA STARTING TO PANIC.
YOU CAN SEE IT IN HER FACE.
L.J. WITH HIS THIRD PIECE.
L.J. WITH THE FOURTH PIECE FOR
THE BEAUTY TRIBE.
HE'S STARTING TO PULL AWAY NOW.
YOU WOULD THINK THIS IS WHERE
THE BRAIN TRIBE WOULD DO WELL.
>> THEY'RE STILL WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> I THINK I'M ON THE WRONG
TRIBE HERE.
>> Jeff: L.J. WITH THE FIFTH
PIECE FOR THE BEAUTY TRIBE.
J'TIA HAS HER SECOND PIECE NEW.
>> FOCUS ON ONE OF THOSE TWO.
>> Jeff: BEAUTY WITH THEIR
SIXTH PIECE.
THEY HAVE TWO PIECES LEFT J'TIA
ONLY WITH TWO PIECES COMPLETED.
J'TIA CAN FEEL IT COMING.
BEAUTY WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
THEY'RE SAFE FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL
COUNCIL.
FOR THE SECOND TIME IN A ROW,
BRAINS WILL VOTE SOMEBODY OUT.
BRAWN TRIBE, CONGRATULATIONS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
BEAUTY TRIBE, I DON'T KNOW HOW
YOU PULLED IT OUT, BUT DID YOU.
>> L.J., IT'S ALL YOU.
>> Jeff: IMMUNITY FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
J'TIA, YOUR BODY LANGUAGE SAYS
IT ALL.
WHAT ARE YOU FEELING RIGHT NOW?
I FEEL LIKE I LET MY TRIBE DOWN.
USUALLY I'M REALLY GOOD AT
PUZZLES, AND I FAILED.
>> Jeff: REPORTER, BRAWN
TRIBE, GRAB YOUR HUGE FISHING
REWARD.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
BEAUTY TRIBE, COME GET YOUR
FISHING REWARD.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
ALL RIGHT, BRAIN TRIBE, FOR THE
SECOND TIME, TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> YEAH!
VICTORY IS SWEET.
>> SHE SEALED THE DEAL AGAIN.
>> TODAY WE GO TO THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AND JUST SLICED MY
FINGER RIGHT OPEN.
TONY SLICED HIS FOOT LIKE A DUMB
ASS.
THERE WAS BLOOD ON THE PUZZLE.
THAT'S THE BRAWN TRIBE FOR YOU.
THAT'S WHAT WE DO, BLOOD, SWEAT,
AND TEARS AND WE GET THE JOB
DONE.
>> DID YOU THERE, EVERYONE.
>> NICE WORK.
WE PREVAILED.
WE WON THE FISHING GEAR.
WE WON THE WHOLE WORKS.
WE HAVE OLIVE OIL.
WE HAVE SEA SALT.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL THING.
THIS IS GOOD STUFF.
THE FIRST THING THAT POPPED INTO
MY MIND THERE HAS TO BE SOME
KIND OF IDOL OR CLUE TO AN IDOL
THERE THAT BASKET.
I OPENED UP THE WOODEN TACKLE
BOX, AND I SEE A LITTLE PIECE
OF-- A LITTLE PIECE OF PAPER IN
THERE.
SO WHEN I WENT BACK INTO THE
BASKET, I TOOK IT OUT AND PUT IT
IN MY POCKET, AND THIS IS WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
"THE OCEAN OFFERS FISH.
YOUR WELL OFFERS DRINK.
ANOTHER BODY OF WATER OFFERS
PROTECTION, AND PROTECTION IS
WHAT I NEED RIGHT NOW.
TIED TO SOMETHING SOLID IS THE
IDOL YOU WANT TO GET, VERY
HIDDEN BUT NOT TOO DEEP, AND
REQUIRES THAT YOU GET WET."
I LOVE IT.
AND I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE THIS
THING IS.
IT'S IN THE POND THAT WE HAVE
BEHIND CAMP, AND THERE'S A BIG,
BIG MONSTER LOG, AND THAT'S
SOLID.
I LOVE YOU.
LOVE IT.
COME ON, MAN.
OOOH!
OH!
IT'S OVER NOW, BABY.
THIS IS UNREAL, MAN.
COME ON, MAN.
I WENT RIGHT INTO THE LAKE, AND
FINALLY I FELT A LUMP, AND SURE
ENOUGH, THERE WAS AN IDOL RIGHT
THERE, AND I FOUND IT.
THIS IS HUGE.
I NEEDED THIS.
OH!
OOOOOOH!
OOOOOH!
OOOOH!
OH!
I DON'T NEED TO TELL ANYBODY
ABOUT THE IDOL.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BENEFIT ME IN
ANY WAY TO TELL ANYBODY ABOUT
THE IDOL.
THAT WILL GIVE THEM LEVERAGE TO
SNEAK ATTACK ME AND I DON'T WANT
THAT.
I'D RATHER SNEAK ATTACK THEM.
THE IDOL, NOBODY WILL KNOW ABOUT
THAT.
I'M KING OF THE JUNGLE.
KING OF THE JUNGLE.
I'M KING OF THE JUNGLE!
>> SO WE GET BACK TO CAMP, AND
GIVEN THE FACT THAT J'TIA
TOTALLY SCREWED UP THE WHOLE
CHALLENGE, IT'S CLEAR TGERMANY'S
THE BEST OPTION TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING WE
SHOULD DO?
HAVE, LIKE, 100 SIDE
CONVERSATIONS OR SHOULD WE TRY
AND FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO AS A
GROUP?
>> I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO
ACTUALLY PLAY THE IDOL AT
TRIBAL, SO I JUST DECIDED TO TRY
TO GET KASS TO REPRESENT HER
LOYALTIES IN FRONT OF EVERYONE
TO SEE WHERE SHE WAS AT.
KASS?
YOU HAVE ANY OPINION?
>> I THINK J'TIA.
I MEAN, SHE BACKSTROKED ALL THE
WAY BACK WHILE WE WERE PULLING
THE STUFF.
AND THEN THE PUZ PUZZLE.
I MEAN, THERE WASN'T ONE
CONTRIBUTION TO THE CHALLENGE IN
ANY ASPECT.
I'M JUST BEING HONEST.
>> SPENCER, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I MEAN, YEAH, IT MAKES SENSE.
ARE WE JUST, LIKE, HAVING AN
OPEN FORUM RIGHT NOW?
>> I THINK WE SHOULD TALK.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD BE OPEN
ABOUT IT, YEAH, AS OPPOSED TO-
>> I MEAN, WE DO NEED TO WIN.
GARRETT?
>> YEAH, I AGREE.
TASHA?
>> YEAH, I STILL KIND OF JUST
WANT TO TALK TO PEOPLE AND--
JUST INDIVIDUALLY BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW, I DON'T KNOW THAT WE'RE
BEING AS CANDID AS POSSIBLE.
>> LOOK, MY VOTE IS TO, LIKE,
NOT HAVE SIDE CONVOS, HONESTLY.
THAT IS WHAT I WOULD PREFER.
>> I ABSOLUTELY LOVE "SURVIVOR"
AND NOW THAT I'M HERE IT'S
FRUSTRATING TO PLAY WITH PEOPLE
THAT DON'T WANT TO PLAY THE
GAME.
YOU KNOW, I LOOKED FORWARD TO
SCHEMING AND BACKSTABBING, BUT
APPARENTLY, I'M BEING TOLD NO.
IT SADDENS ME.
>> BEST CASE, I THINK, IS THE
FIVE OF US SIT HERE TOGETHER
UNTIL TRIBAL.
WE EAT DINNER--
>> I NEED TO TALK TO YOU TWO.
THAT'S THE ONLY SIDE
CONVERSATION I NEED TO HAVE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY WE NEED TO
TALK SEPARATELY.
IT'S ALL BEEN-- IT'S ALL OUT IN
THE OPEN.
>> THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
LIKE, YOU GO TALK.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT
ANYMORE.
I DON'T--
>> THEN QUIT!
JUST-- THIS IS-- I MEAN, IT'S--
THIS IS, LIKE, THE LEAST
STRATEGIC GAME I HAVE EVER
PLAYED.
I DON'T KNOW WHY GARRETT THINKS
HE IS THE AUTHORITY AT LUZON.
HE IS THE NOTHE LEADER AT THIS
TRIBE.
HE LAYS AROUND ALL DAY, PRETTY
MUCH WATCHES EVERYONE WORK.
HE'S ALWAYS HUNGRY, AND NOW HE
DOESN'T EVEN WANT TO PLAY THE
GAME.
IT'S JUST-- IT'S SILLY.
IT'S REALLY SILLY.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
IF YOU DIDN'T WANT TO PLAY THE
GAME HOW IT SHOULD BE PLAYED,
GET-- GET OUT OF HERE!
GET OUT OF HERE " OF HERE.
>> SO MY TRIBE SAT ME DOWN AND
TOLD ME, SIT DOWN RIGHT HERE.
WELL, WE'VE BEEN REVIEWING YOUR
FILE, AND WE THINK YOU HAVE TO
GO.
NO, NO, NO I'M NOT-- I'LL JUST
TELL YOU FROM THE WHOLE COMPANY.
YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT IN MY PERSONALITY MADE YOU
THINK THAT WAS GOING TO WORK?
>> IT'S JUST NOT ABOUT TODAY.
IT'S ABOUT THE NEXT THREE DAYS,
AND THE--
>> THE NEXT THREE TASE WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE A GREAT CAMP AND
WIN A CHALLENGE.
>> YOU'LL WIN ALL THE CHALLENGES
BACK TO BACK AND NEVER HAVE TO
GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL AGAIN.
>> CAN'T EVEN STRATEGIZE.
>> LIKE, THE "SURVIVOR" GENIUS
HE IS, GARRETT DECIDES TO HAVE
AN OPEN FORUM ON WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO LATER AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
GARRETT, YOU'RE AN IDIOT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE A FIRST-CLASS, GRADE-A
MORON IN "SURVIVOR."
WHY WOULD DO YOU THAT?
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN SO EASY TO
TELL J'TIA WHAT SHE WANTS TO
HEAR, BUT NOW THAT GARRETT PUT
IT OUT IN THE OPEN WE HAVE TO
BABY SIT THESE GIRLS AND MAKE
SURE THEY GO HOME.
>> HEY, IF THEY DON'T WANT TO
SCRAMBLE, I'M GOING TO SCRAMBLE
AND TRY TO TWIST THIS GAME UP.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT TRYING TO GO
HOME NEXT.
>> THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S ONE AND TWO.
EITHER I'M THREE OR FOUR OR
YOU'RE THREE OR FOUR.
I NEED TO WORK MY WAY TO THE
TOP.
WHY CAN'T I BE TOP DOG?
I CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN?
I'M TELLING YOU, ONE AND TWO.
TODAY IS THE ONLY DAY WE HAVE
THE NUMBERS.
KASS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HAY, I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE
J'TIA ALONE.
GOD KNOWS WHAT SHE'S DOING
THERE.
>> SHE PISSED.
>> SOMEBODY NEEDS TO WATCH HER.
>> WHO KNOWS WHAT SHENAN GRANS
GOING ON?
>> THERE ARE NO SHENANIGANS.
>> I DON'T MIND FTHAT'S WHAT IT
HAS TO COME TO, I'M DOWN FOR IT.
I'M COMING IN HOT.
IT'S GOING TO BE GUNS TBLAIZING.
I'M COMING IN LIKE A CRAZY
PERSON.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE GUARDING ME.
I'M LIKE THE MENTAL PATIENT.
AND THEY LEFT THE MENTAL PATIENT
ALONE AND SHE WENT CRAZY!
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
LEAVE CRAZY PEOPLE ALONE.
>> WE DON'T HAVE ANY WATER IN
ANY OF THE BOTTLES?
>> NOTHING.
>> THINK ABOUT IT.
>> WHERE DID ALL THAT RICE COME
FROM?
WHO POURED RICE ON THE FIRE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THE RICE FAIRY?
>> I DON'T UPON.
>> THERE'S RICE ON THE FIRE.
>> HELLO!
>> IS THAT ALL THE RICE?
>> WHO KNOWS WHAT SHE DID.
>> IT'S ALL GONE.
>> I CANNOT--
>> THIS RICE IS, LIKE, ALMOST
ALL GONE.
J'TIA WAS SOMEWHAT SUBDUED WHEN
WE ALL BEHIND WNT DOWN TO THE
BEACH WHEN WAS A MISTAKE AND
THEN SHE DUMPED OUR RICE OUT AND
NOW WE HAVE NO RICE.
I'VE HAD SUCH A HARD TIME OUT
HERE ALREADY, IT JUST BRINGS ME
TO A NEW ROCK BOTTOM.
LOOK.
GARRETT.
ALL OF OUR RICE.
>> I WANTED US ALL TO STAY
TOGETHER UP HERE!
>> HOW DID WE COME UP WITH THE
CRITERIA FOR BRAINS?
I'D LIKE TO SEE THAT DATA.
BECAUSE, UH, IRONICALLY, I WAS
GOING TO APPROACH J'TIA ABOUT
TURNING THIS AROUND.
BUT THEN I GET BACK TO CAMP, AND
SHE JUST POURED ALL OF OUR RICE
ON THE FIRE.
I CAN'T ALIGN WITH SOMEONE LIKE
THAT.
>> Jeff: TRIBAL COUNCIL NUMBER
TWO.
THE LOOKS ON YOUR FACES RIGHT
NOW.
SPENCER, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> AFTER THE CHALLENGE, WE
DECIDE TO HAVE AN OPEN FORUM
DISCUSSION OF THE VOTE-OUT,
WHICH IS USUALLY NOT WHAT YOU DO
IN "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: SO TELL ME ABOUT THE
DISCUSSION, TASHA.
>> YOU KNOW, WE WERE PRETTY
CAPPEDID ABOUT WHERE WE LOST THE
CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: AND WAS THAT BLAME
J'TIA.
>> YEAH, I SUGGESTED HEY,
SPENCER, HEY, GARRETT, CAN WE
JUST GO TALK.
BUT THEN GARRETT MADE THE
SUGGESTIONS, NO, LET'S ALL JUST
TALK RIGHT HERE.
>> Jeff: GARRETT YWHY HAVE
THIS OPEN DISCUSSION?
WHAT IS THE BASIS FOR THAT?
>> I WANTED KASS TON WE WERE
ANYTHING TO BE WORK HER, AND I
WANTED HER TO SAY THAT WE WERE
GOING TO VOTE WITH J'TIA AND WE
WERE WITH KASS AND THAT WOULD
CALM HER NERVES.
>> I ASKED WHY GARRETT GOT TO
CALL ALL THE SHOTS AND I THREW
THE RICE IN THE FIRE.
>> Jeff: WOW.
ALL THE RICE?
>> MOST OF IT.
>> JUST ABOUT.
>> LIKE, LITERALLY, 98% OF IT.
>> YEAH, NOT MY BEST MOMENT.
NOT AT ALL.
>> BUT, JEFF, I CAN ADD, THAT'S
WHY I WANTED TO HAVE THE
CONVERSATION PRIVATELY.
SHE'S VOLATILE.
I KNEW THAT WE WERE HEADING DOWN
THE WRONG TRACK WITH THIS ONE.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS ARE
RESPONSIBLE FOR TELLING HER SHE
WAS GOING HOME.
THERE'S A REASON BLINDSIDES
WORK.
IT'S NOT BECAUSE THEY'RE FUN.
IT'S BECAUSE THEY'RE EFFECTIVE.
>> THE ONLY THING GOING OUT AND
HAVING MORE CONVERSATIONS ABOUT
IT DOES IS PUT OUR "SURVIVOR"
GAME AT STAKE.
I WAS NEVER TRYING TO MASTERMIND
ANYTHING.
>> BASICALLY, YOU PUT ME OVER
YOUR KNEE AND SPANKED MY ASS IN
FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
>> THAT'S WILDLY UNTRUE.
>> OKAY.
>> AT THIS POINT, SHE'S GOING
HOME, AND SHE DESTROYS 98% OF
OUR RICE, AND BY PAINTING ME IN
A NEGATIVE LIGHT IN FRONT OF MY
TRIBE MATES IS VERY UNFAIR.
>> Jeff: KASS, WHERE DO YOU
FALL ON THIS?
YOU HEARD TWO SIDES NOW, J'TIA
AND GARRETT?
>> JEFF, THESE PEOPLE ARE ALL SO
PARANOID.
I WAS DOWN AT THE WATER WITH
TASHA WASHING OUR FEET AFTER THE
CHALLENGE AND GATOR WAS SO
PARANOID HE CAME DOWN TO THE
WATER AND THEN THE RICE GOT
POURED OUT.
>> THAT'S NOT FAIR.
>> IT'S THE RICE AND IT'S GONE.
>> IF YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO HAVE
A TALK RIGHT BEFORE TRIBAL
COUNCIL, YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME TO
JUST SIT THERE.
>> WHAT WAS MORE IMPORTANT, 30
DAYS' WORTH OF RICE OR WATCHING
US WASH OUR FEET?
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> JEFF, I FEEL LIKE MY GAME IS
BEING STIFLED RIGHT NOW,
LITERALLY STIFLED.
HOW CAN YOU PLAY "SURVIVOR" WHEN
YOU CAN'T HAVE CONVERSATIONS?
>> TASHA WAS UTSET TODAY BECAUSE
J'TIA WAS HER CLOSEST ALLY.
IT'S REALLY THAT SIMPLE.
YOU CAN ASK THE OTHERS IN THE
ALLIANCE-- I'M SORRY, IN THE
TRIBE.
SO WE WANT J'TIA TOOK.
OF COURSE THAT'S GOING TO UPSET
HER.
>> Jeff: KASS, YOU CHUCKLED
WHEN HE SAID "ALLIANCE" AND
FIXED IT BY SAYING "TRIBE."
>> BECAUSE I'M NOT IN THE
ALLIANCE.
>> YOU DON'T THINK YOU, SPENCER,
AND I WORKED OUT AN ALLIANCE ON
DAY FOUR.
>> OH, YOU'RE OUT.
>> NOW I'M OUT.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> SO IT IS FLEXIBLE.
AND GARRETT DECIDES WHO'S IN AND
OUT.
>> Jeff: SO IF I HAVE IT
RIGHT, THE WAY IT SITS NOW IS
IT'S GARRETT, KASS, AND SPENCER
IN AN ALLIANCE.
J'TIA AND TASHA ARE IN TROUBLE.
J'TIA IS PROBABLY GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> I DON'T SEE IT THAT WAY AT
ALL.
>> Jeff: ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU
JUST SAID?
>> IF J'TIA GOES HOME.
WE HAVE FOUR PLAYERS, ALL OF
WHOM CAN BE ONE STRONG TEAM.
>> Jeff: MAYBE I'M
MALNOURISHED, SPENCER, AM I
WRONG?
>> YOU'RE NOT WRONG, THAT'S
EXACTLY WHAT I SAID.
>> WHEN KASS CAME TO SPENCER AND
I AND SAID, "YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
BE ABLE TO BREAK YOU WANT GIRLS,
AND SPENCER AND I THOUGHT, OKAY,
YEAH, THAT MAKES SENSE.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WE WERE
GOING TO DO.
BUT WHEN J'TIA FAILED AT THE
PUZZLE IN THE CHALLENGE, THE
DECISION BECAME CLEAR WHAT WE
SHOULD DO.
>> Jeff: NOW, KASS, GARRETT
HAS JUST SAID YOU WENT TO HIM
AND SPENCER AND SAID LET'S BREAK
YOU WANT WOMEN AND FORM OUR OWN
ALLIANCE TRUE OR FALSE?
>> GARRETT SAID THAT.
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WENT DOWN.
>> Jeff: HOW DO YOU TRUST
GARRETT?
>> HOW DO YOU TRUST ANYBODY?
>> I'M OUT OF THE ALLIANCE, IT'S
NOT TRUE.
WE NEEDED TO SPLIT YOU UP,
TASHA, THAT'S ALL.
THE FOUR OF US ARE ALL EQUAL.
>> WHICH FOUR?
>> Jeff: MAN, NECESSARY NUTS.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IS ABOUT
TO HAPPEN BUT IT'S BEEN VERY
ENLIGHTENING, AND IT'S BEEN
CRAZY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
GARRETT, YOU'RE UP.
>> THE FACT THAT YOU'RE A
NUCLEAR ?RNLG GENUINELY,
GENUINELY SCARY.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IN ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE.
J'TIA.
GARRETT.
ONE VOTE J'TIA, ONE VOTE
THAT'S TWO VOTES J'TIA, ONE VOTE
GARRETT.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES J'TIA, TWO VOTES
GARRETT, ONE VOTE LEFT.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN," GARRETT.
GARRETT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> WHO WANTS TO WELCOME ME TO
THE BOTTOM?
>> IT'S NOT SO BAD.
>> Jeff: WELL, THIS IS THE
ODDEST TRIBE I HAVE EVER SEEN.
IF THERE'S ANYTHING GOOD THAT
CAME OUT OF TONIGHT'S TRIBAL,
IT'S THAT IT APPEARS YOU'RE
FINALLY LEARNING HOW TO PLAY THE
GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> TONIGHT SELOOKING FOR AN
ALLY.
WHILE EVERYONE ELSE-- IS JUST
LOOKING.
>> IT'S AWFUL.
>> Jeff: TO HANG ON.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN IN A
"SURVIVOR" NIGHTMARE.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
I WAS SO BLINDSIDED.
I WAS SO SURE I KNEW WHAT WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN TONIGHT.
IT'S REALLY EMBARRASSING IN A
LOT OF DIFFERENT WAYS, REALLY,
REALLY EMBARRASSING.