translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Brice, the tribe has spoken.
In the Beauty tribe,
Morgan lost his only ally .
and found himself facing
an alliance of four.
It is very likely
that I will leave next.
I'll have to save
myself, I guess.
In the Muscle tribe,
winning was becoming routine.
The Muscle Tribe succeeds!
But that did not prevent
divisions from appearing.
I want Cliff gone.
I can do it.
Trust me.
During the last
immunity test...
Spencer, it goes in and it comes out!
The Intelligence tribe
perpetuates its tradition…
She is there! Muscle wins!
...of defeat.
The Intelligence tribe
once again goes to the council.
- And at the tribal council...
- At this rate,
none of you will be there at the end.
- Nope.
- ...their dilemma was clear.
Do we keep the strongest
to the trials, Spencer?
Or do we choose
the one who has proven her loyalty?
Finally,
they chose strength.
J'Tia, bring me your torch.
J'Tia, the tribe has spoken.
There are fourteen left,
who will be eliminated tonight?
It's a sign.
Our fire is still burning.
- Oh my God.
- Okay, hugs?
- To both of you.
- It was really intense.
- Oh my God.
- I've never been so nervous.
I couldn't
be happier
to always be in the game.
I was thinking of leaving today.
This game changes in an instant.
Now I'm going back.
It's like a roller coaster
and I'm glad I haven't
fallen off the wagon yet.
I don't know
what made your decision.
I can't... You...
It's intense, making
the decisions during the council.
I knew that by keeping her,
we would be back three days
later, with regrets.
- Absolutely.
- I had that feeling.
This advice was crazy.
We had a
last minute vote change.
I suddenly realized
that we guaranteed a defeat
if we kept J'Tia.
But if we took Spencer,
he delivers.
And I need to win.
But our way of playing
is ridiculous.
We are not "Intelligence",
one is "Imbecility".
We're a messy dead end
with a handful of nerds at heart.
We could be the final trio.
The only thing that separates us from it,
it's two whole tribes.
That's all?
- That's all.
- No problem.
What's new?
- How much?
- The rice is thrown.
How about we look at
what the mail says?
- Yes!
- I knew it.
“You dream of tasting victory.
Or so it seems.
Will this flavor
be denied to you?
You will struggle and scream
as you are dragged away."
- To eat.
- A test with food.
The decision to keep Spencer
will be tested today.
We keep telling ourselves that it
's the best combination of people,
that it is the strongest tribe
that we have had.
Today, we will be fixed.
- This is the opportunity to come back.
- Yes.
The start of the return.
The Intelligence tribe
really had a hard time,
and if we win,
I think people
will start wondering again
what is the true strength
of our tribe.
Over here, everyone!
Muscle and Beauty Tribes,
discover the new
Intelligence tribe.
J'Tia was eliminated
at the last council.
Alright, everyone.
Throw away your bandanas.
Intelligence, Muscle
and Beauty no longer exist.
Damn it.
We will form
two new tribes.
Oh my God.
Jeff said, "Throw away your bandanas,"
and my head went...
It took me six days to
figure out who to trust.
And now
I have to start all over again.
You're all going to take
a wrapped bandana.
Don't open it yet.
Take whatever you want.
I'm nervous.
We are forming two new
ones - Aparri and Solana.
- OK.
- So it will be orange or purple.
Open all your little package
and see which bandana you have.
Intelligence stays together.
Many members of Muscle
stick together.
- Good.
- We all have the same.
Take a seat on your new mats.
Meet
your new teammates.
Health!
Nice to meet you.
Alexis, delighted.
Lindsey. You must be LJ.
- Nice to meet you.
- I am Jefra.
Well, we have
our two new tribes.
The New Solana Tribe:
Sarah, you are the only one
of your tribe left.
What do you think
of this new tribe?
I feel
like the exception.
My whole tribe has just left me.
Tasha, that's exactly
what you called for.
- A new beginning.
- In effect.
I'm very excited.
I think this tribe will be
very strong in the trials.
I'm really excited, Jeff.
- Jefra.
- Yes sir?
Almost the whole Muscle tribe
is together, and there's LJ and you.
- Yes.
- What are you doing now?
Our position sucks.
They are more numerous than us,
but I'm excited
to be with Muscle.
They are supposed to be
the best, the strongest,
and there might be
a place for LJ and me.
Cliff, what's the impact on the game?
It changes
people's thinking mechanisms,
on their position and their alliances,
if they will continue
to make these alliances work
or create new ones.
Well, how about we
go to our first
reward trial
as new tribes?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Today a person
will hold on to a pole.
On my signal,
two members of the other tribe
will try to unhook
this person from the post
and drag
her to the finish line.
The first tribe to bring back
the member of the other team
to the finish line,
scores a point.
The first team to two points
wins the reward.
- Want to know what's at stake?
- Yeah!
It's big, it's beautiful,
you'll love it.
Coffee, donuts, chocolate cookies,
blueberry pastries,
cinnamon rolls, brownies.
A splendid way to celebrate
the first victory of a new tribe.
A moment to get organized,
and we'll get started.
First round, only women.
Morgan and Sara.
They gon' try to get
Lindsey off that post
and get him to cross the line.
Trish and Jephra.
They will try to get Tasha.
We play in two points.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Tasha and Lindsey
gather their forces.
You can do it, Tasha!
Jefra and Trish attack Tasha.
Sarah and Morgan
tackle Lindsey.
You gotta get 'em off the post
and bring them back to the sand.
They freed
Lindsey's arms.
Morgan sits on Lindsey
while Sarah
takes care of the feet.
Come on, Tasha!
Tasha clings.
Trish and Jefra can't
get her to move.
- She is well attached.
- Hold on, Tasha!
- Fight!
- So.
Sarah cleared
Lindsey's legs.
Morgan and Sarah took
Lindsey off the post.
Now we have to bring her back.
Lindsey hangs on again.
It gets very physical
between Lindsey, Morgan and Sarah.
Trish and Jefra picked up
both of Tasha's arms off the pole.
Morgan and Sarah took
Lindsey off the post,
but she clings to the sand.
Lindsey makes it difficult
for Morgan and Sarah.
It's a great first battle.
Sarah and Morgan
slowly take Lindsey away
towards the finish line.
But she makes a very big effort.
Lindsey is on her feet again.
And again on the ground.
Tasha is locked.
Trish and Jefra fail
to get her.
Sarah and Morgan are
ever closer
to get
Lindsey across the line.
That's it, Aparri
scores the first point!
Two men, one woman.
They will try to unhook
Cliff from the post.
LJ et Trish.
They will try to get
Alexis off the post.
Aparri leads 1-0.
We play in 2 points.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Cliff is tall.
It is heavy, it is high,
it is massive.
Jeremiah and Spencer
don't hesitate for a moment.
Alexis is no match,
it seems unfair.
LJ drags her.
Alexis, very quickly
unhooked from the post.
She struggles,
but that won't change anything.
Lo and behold, Solana scores.
Tied, 1-1.
Two men, one woman.
Each tribe fields
its strongest players.
Cliff finds the post for Solana.
And attacking Sarah,
Lindsey and Tony.
The winners of this round
earn the reward.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Come on, Spencer!
It's decided now,
give it all you got,
to hold on or to drop out.
Depending on your role.
Lindsey keeps
both of Sarah's arms unhooked.
Tony unhooked his legs.
Spencer and Jeremiah
unhooked Cliff's arms.
Spencer tries
to clinch her legs.
This time, Spencer and Jeremiah
progress a bit.
But Cliff's feet
are locked.
Sarah struggles hard
against Tony and Lindsey.
They drag her, but
she makes it difficult for them.
Spencer tries to clinch
Cliff's feet.
Jeremiah is sitting on Cliff.
Tony picks up Sarah.
He literally lifts her up.
Cliff remains lying down,
as if to say "go ahead!".
Try!
- Go on!
- Come on, Tony!
Sarah fights back.
She does not give up.
Sarah gives time
to Spencer and Jeremiah,
and it works.
Spencer released
Cliff's feet.
Tony shoots Sarah again.
She lost her two shoes.
The reward is near.
Solana could win.
And that's it!
Solana wins the reward!
Huge physical effort
from everyone.
Solana, congratulations.
Take your reward,
return to camp and enjoy.
Apparri, I have nothing for you.
Grab your things
and head back to camp.
It's nice to go
from mothers to pretty daughters,
but it's also hard
to lose all the time.
Everything related to Intelligence
seems
to be going wrong somehow.
Nice job on that first
reward, folks!
Damn, look at this shelter!
That's either the tarp
or Cliff's jacket.
We won the race,
good news.
But in reality,
this is bad news.
Be careful, don't eat too fast.
Jefra and I are in the minority,
at 5-2, against the Muscle tribe.
I have an idol
that I could play,
but it would just
save me a few days,
and then I would leave.
My only hope
is that they absorb me
as a teammate,
rather than a threat.
We're trying to guess
what you're doing.
In your opinion?
- Are you a hairdresser?
- Yeah.
The scissors.
You
must be a professional surfer.
I am a surf
and martial arts coach.
- You are a horse trainer.
- Yeah.
Where do you come from?
I'd never thought...
I thought you were
from Montana or Colorado.
I found out that LJ
is from Massachusetts,
which I would not have guessed.
I'm coming too.
It creates a bond between us.
You were in Saugus High School?
- When did you graduate?
- 97.
I thought those in Beauty were
spending time on their looks.
But LJ is pretty laid back
and easy going.
And you can tell he's a gentleman.
He's from Boston,
that must be why
I immediately found him cute.
I found myself single,
and I said to myself "I want a horse".
- And when I got him...
- Are you single?
- Yes, single.
- Oh, oh, Trish!
- Oh, shut up!
- Single!
I find LJ very handsome,
but I could be his mother.
I am not Mrs. Robinson.
It's perfect.
We have a small island.
When Trish said
she was from Boston,
it was a ray
of sunshine for me.
There is already a bond between us,
and if i were to be attracted
to someone a little older,
a bachelor who should have lived,
Whether she's attracted to
my sex appeal or something,
I will use it to save myself.
I should go out more.
I didn't know about twerking.
I would like to hear Trish roar.
No, nobody wants to
hear me roar, believe me!
Trish exaggerates her laugh
when she's with guys,
and that disgusts me.
You're 50, stop trying
to attract the attention
of 20-year-old men.
Seriously.
Things couldn't
have turned out better today.
"come on!".
Amazing, all those purples.
I'm happy
with this mix of tribes.
I was able to keep five
of my original team-mates.
If we can keep
moving forward with these people,
we are in an excellent position.
The only thing I hated
was when Trish got purple.
Right now,
my concern is Trish.
I don't know what
's going on between her and LJ.
I have to keep an eye on them.
It's imperative.
- High five!
- Here, my friend!
What a beautiful shelter!
If I had known
that we would have visitors,
I would have cleaned up.
Our laundry is hanging everywhere.
You are at home,
you are not guests.
Get comfortable.
I am the only
original Aparri in the tribe,
with three members of Intelligence
and three of Beauty.
This is clearly
a worrying situation.
Because we don't know
who we can trust.
That's why I wanted to
know who, on the first day,
had the clue for the idol,
or chose the food.
We have two bags of rice here.
Thanks to Trish.
Trish didn't choose the clue,
but the rice.
- She chose a second bag?
- So Garret chose the clue?
He didn't tell us anything.
He told us
there was a decision.
- We were going to ask.
- Yeah.
What was the decision?
Rice or the idol?
- You're kidding?
- No, that was it.
I did not find it.
- Oh, you looked for the idol?
- Yes.
Sarah revealed to me,
when she said Trish
preferred rice to idol.
I had chosen the clue
and kept it a secret ever since.
I hope I can make
a new start with this tribe
and let no
one hold it against me.
It was a clue for the idol
or a bag of rice.
I looked for the idol.
But obviously I don't.
My God!
Morgan lied
from day one.
It made her even
more suspicious than before.
Like she was carrying
a hundred red flags.
They told me exactly
what I needed to know:
that you should neither
trust her nor ally herself with her.
So I will protect myself
and switch sides immediately.
I would like to consider
a few scenarios with you.
My closest friend
in my tribe was Jefra.
And she's not here.
So I think
the only safe scenario
would be that we allied,
all four.
I don't know
if you're in,
and it's hard to
immediately trust.
But I give you my word,
I'm serious.
That Alexis came to see us
so fast, almost desperate,
is telling.
Now that we see a little
of the divisions of Beauty,
it greatly improves
the position of Intelligence.
The fact that they're so divided
shows that they can be played
against each other.
Initially,
Jeremiah was with us,
but he changed sides,
then changed sides again.
And Morgan lies all the time.
In the whole game, she
never went to fetch water.
She had to pick up
two pieces of wood.
The Beauty tribe
loves gossip.
It feels like high school.
They gossip about each other,
spread rumours.
Sometimes in front of each other.
She and LJ cuddle
every night.
He always asks her
to move her buttocks.
Butt wiggling, yeah!
She is proud to know how to
move her ass like that.
They seem singularly lacking
in social skills
for a tribe of
supposedly beautiful and sociable people.
My instinct tells me
that Morgan wouldn't hesitate
to betray me.
Really?
Are you and Alexis friends?
We were at the start.
LJ, her and I, we were like that.
So I'm away.
Do you see
what I mean?
I will follow you.
On bolts to ground four.
For now, Intelligence is
in the best possible position.
At first, I thought
we should face Beauty,
but there are
dissensions between them.
So we went from tragedy
to what appears to be a triumph.
Just when you think you're lost,
things change.
And you're back on top.
The night of this big storm,
were you cold?
- That was crazy, right?
- I no longer felt my extremities.
Me too, I didn't feel
my toes for 3 hours.
I felt so good,
before the change,
my position was solid.
But with just LJ and me,
and the whole Muscle tribe,
the feeling
is totally different.
- I'll give you a quick rundown.
- Yes, what's going on?
Lindsey and I are not...
We are not in...
- You're not on the same side?
- No no no.
You understood that quickly, huh?
She will make you feel like
you are working hard.
- OK.
- But this is not the case.
She is allied with Cliff.
- Lindsey and Cliff?
- Yes.
When Trish
summed up alliances for me
and explained his position to me,
it was a bit surprising,
because it happened rather quickly.
I won't sell
the bear skin until I kill it,
but there may be a space
where LJ and I could sneak.
There's something
fishy about Cliff.
We wanted to get rid of it,
but we couldn't lose the race.
LJ is clearly with me,
we are very close.
I was very naive at the start of the game.
But I'm starting to realize
that I have to do what it takes
to get to the top.
OK, we agree.
From the start, I thought I
was the most misplaced.
But everything was turned upside down.
Hi big guy!
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all,
I take back the idols.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
As of now, we only play
for an immunity idol.
We're going to get rid
of the little brother.
And we keep Mom.
Your Dad.
I'm not really sure.
Today each tribe
will use a large trunk
to knock down two walls.
Then you will maneuver the trunk
through a maze.
The first tribe
to cross the labyrinth
and ring the gong
wins immunity
and is shielded from the vote.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be
the fifth person eliminated
from Survivor Cagayan.
This event is played
six against six.
In each tribe,
someone will not participate.
- It will be me.
- Trish is not participating for Solana.
What about you, Apparri?
Are you good
at puzzles and mazes?
- I want to participate.
- Me too.
Do we do paper, rock, scissors?
I really want to participate.
Who will it be?
Do paper, stone, scissors.
- Go for it.
- OK.
Paper, stone, scissors.
The pebble breaks the scissors.
Morgan, take a seat on the bench.
Alexis will participate.
One minute to get organized,
and we'll get started.
Well, on and go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
The six must hold
the trunk permanently.
From the outset, it's neck and neck.
Use the trunk
to break down this wall.
It's not conclusive for Solana.
Apparri, it's harder
than it looks, isn't it?
It's harder
than you thought.
You have to lift the trunk
more to hit higher.
Solana does some damage,
here we go.
Apari insists.
But they have trouble
lifting the trunk.
You can cross,
as long as you don't let go of the trunk.
Solana makes the crossing easier.
- Can we switch places?
- Yes.
Yes, you can switch places.
Aparri will change strategy
and put the tough ones in the front.
Solana has crossed the first wall.
Aparri is still
on the first wall.
There are two to cross.
Solana attacked her second wall.
It takes a lot of strength.
The trunks are heavy.
The walls are very strong.
Sarah crosses.
Aparri passes to the second wall.
Aparri is in on it again.
Solana lost momentum.
Aparri changed strategy,
with Jeremiah and Spencer,
and it works.
Aparri begins to cross.
Solana now crosses.
It's neck and neck,
it's going to be played out in the maze.
- Go! Go! Go!
- Let's go!
- Gently.
- This way.
Once the trunk is in place,
remove the handles
and start the maze.
Solana attacks the maze.
Aparri attacks
the maze now.
PUSH!
Left! Right! Left!
Solana has a slight lead.
But Aparri is right behind.
PUSH! PUSH!
Back up, back up, back up!
Solana makes a big mistake,
they have to back off.
No no no!
Step back, step back!
Aparri makes the same mistake.
They must back down.
Lots of teamwork.
Communication is crucial.
Solana brought out the front.
Also appeared.
Is it correct?
This is where the Intelligence tribe,
which is entirely
at Aparri, should shine.
don't want to go back
to tribal council.
No one from the Muscle Tribe
has gone to the council yet.
- PUSH!
- Aparri is very close.
Solana is now very close.
It's neck and neck again.
- PUSH!
- Go on!
- Yes.
Apparri crossed!
Huge victory for the underdogs!
Aparri wins immunity!
My God!
It was awesome!
We communicated and we did it!
My God!
How it happened?
Apparri, who wants her?
Give it to Tash.
Immunity for Aparri,
no tribal council,
which is a big change
for Tash, Kass and Spencer.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Enjoy your free evening.
Well, Solana, see
you tonight at the council,
where someone will be the fifth
person eliminated from Survivor Cagayan.
Take your things,
return to camp.
How did we
lose this race?
She was made for Muscle.
Fortunately, we have the majority,
things are clear.
LJ is dangerous,
so he leaves first.
It sucks.
What was the thing?
I thought we were in the lead.
I don't know
what happened.
All I know
is that in the end, I was dead.
In the end,
we have to leave it to them,
they beat us.
- I hate losing so much.
- Yeah.
Upon arriving at the test,
"no problem,
it's brute force".
There is no doubt,
we should have won.
Alas, we lost.
And that met Jephra and me
in a difficult position.
They will probably
try to eliminate me.
Unless something
happens, I'm screwed.
I understand it's a game
and that you have
a strong alliance.
But I hope
you will consider
that I can help you.
You know, in trials.
At this point, we can keep LJ
for the trials.
But he's from Massachusetts.
Trish is from Massachusetts.
They have this bond in common.
And they went for walks alone
and had discussions.
She is already playing with her emotions.
And if we get carried away
by our emotions in this game,
that's when we make
silly mistakes.
The four of us will vote for LJ.
- First?
- Light!
I am as good, if not better,
on earth than him,
and ten times better
than him in the water.
So, let's turn the "fort".
Yes, it's over for LJ.
Muscle elders,
we're in a good position.
On our old camp,
there were some tensions,
some problems.
But now
it's a whole new game.
And we have to have
an overview.
And the best for us
is to get rid of LJ.
Alas, paranoia is mounting
at the moment.
Trish does what he wants.
Don't worry about Trish.
He's the kind of person
who likes to be complimented.
Do not worry about that.
Everything is fine for us.
What is their plan?
They want to fire me.
We shouldn't
be seen discussing too much.
But you're in on it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Completely.
We want Cliff gone.
He is really shady.
We have already tried to eliminate it.
- Who exactly?
- Tony and me.
It would be you,
Jefra, me and Tony.
You are in?
Of course, if it's not
my name that comes out.
Exactly.
Well, that's all
we need to know.
Trish told me she wanted
to get rid of Cliff.
I was shocked.
Apparently
Trish and Tony don't like Cliff.
And that makes no sense to me.
You are five against two.
There is nothing to discuss.
But if she is telling the truth?
I may not have
to play my idol.
- That's the plan.
- I hope so, Trish.
You trust me?
Yes. I do not have a choice.
We're from Boston, damn it, okay?
I play with my heart,
and I really like LJ.
He's a gentleman, he gets along
with everyone, he never gives up.
He has it all.
But Cliff, he's not doing anything.
And 14 days of his sufficiency,
it's the most my
nervous system can take.
So we'll write Cliff's name.
And the best part is that
Cliff doesn't suspect a thing.
And that really makes me laugh.
- She's going to betray us.
- But no.
Of course it is, Woo.
I swear on everything I love,
she will fuck us,
I guarantee it.
So what do you think?
And you?
Cliff does nothing.
- I understand.
- He never picked up a piece of wood.
So for me, he goes first.
Do you know that in thirteen days,
he didn't say a word to me?
- I know, but...
- Let's see it this way.
When we merge, we'll have
to fire him anyway.
Because he is strong.
He will kill everyone
in the immunity trials.
By her sheer strength.
He must go.
He leaves first,
and then it will be crazy.
Trish took me aside
and told me he wanted
to get rid of Cliff.
You have to cut off the snake's head.
Which is crazy.
I don't know if she
's bipolar, schizo or what.
But there's no reason
to do that now.
What needs to be done
is get rid of LJ.
He has the heart,
the energy, the ambition,
he has a strategic mind,
so he is dangerous.
Do you trust me
on this one?
I trust you,
but here's what I think.
- Jefra and LJ are isolated.
- Yes.
We are five solids, five solids.
That does not make any sense.
They could get us
one by one if we open that door.
You think Jefra
and LJ are stupid?
- Nope.
- Exactly.
But we could be
the turkeys of the farce.
- We won't.
- OK.
That's the thing. I don't like Cliff.
I never trusted him.
Because Cliff
has a lot of influence.
And he puts people
in his pocket.
Which makes it very dangerous.
More Virer Cliff,
it's all about LJ.
Do I trust him?
Surely not!
So I don't know
what I'm going to do.
What were you discussing?
To stay strong, this and that.
She said she hopes
we stay strong.
So...
You are not trying to...
She said
the dynamic had changed
"I know she has changed."
But if we do something crazy...
Listen. Trish can act
if she wants.
- Not alone.
- Exactly.
If Trish wants to make a hit,
she'll be eliminated.
We need stability.
She can do whatever she wants.
In the end, it's always
four against three.
I know I know.
It's only speculation.
- But who's leaving?
- LJ is leaving.
- LJ.
- OK.
In fact, I'm looking forward
to going to the council.
Trish lets
her emotions rule her.
So we'll cut her off
from her new support,
and bring her back to
her old comrades.
I talked about Cliff with her.
I do not know if that's true.
But we have no way out.
- It's you and me.
- Tony makes me nervous.
Do you think Tony will vote Cliff?
I do not know.
How do you know what's on his mind?
Trish is ready to betray.
The problem is that
I have my doubts about Tony.
But in reality,
I have no choice.
So I fully
trust Trish and Tony
to do
what they said tonight.
And if they start
being too talkative,
I will know if they play
to eliminate me,
and I will play
my idol if necessary.
Those of you who do
n't have a torch, light one.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
When your fire goes out,
it's the end for you.
LJ, after changing tribes,
you return to your camp,
but with only two members,
and five from another tribe.
Who really controls
this camp now?
It was as if Jefra and I
were a couple
who sold his house
and that there was a group
about to buy it.
"When you want us
to leave, let us know."
It was very intimidating
and unpleasant.
But in the end,
it's Jef and me,
and we try to enjoy
it as much as we can.
Cliff, you are coming to
a new camp, but in the majority.
Has life really changed?
It may seem simple, keep
progressing with the majority,
but there will always be someone
who is not comfortable
in his situation,
who can't put
his emotions aside.
And people have to understand
that in this game
majorities are essential.
Ultimately,
that's all that matters.
So, Woo, looks
like Cliff is dreading
that someone in this group
of five does something stupid
and plays with his emotions.
Is this your interpretation?
Yes, I am on this ground.
You can't get carried
away by your emotions.
You have to trust
the group to which you belong.
You have to stay with.
And go against it
will only put you
in a bad situation.
Trish, does this advice
will test the loyalty of the five
former members of Muscle?
I would say yes, absolutely.
Having the majority is important,
but only if it is
of interest to you.
If not, other arrangements may have to be found.
Jefra, it's the only thing
we can want to hear
if we are you or LJ.
That there is a chance.
Maybe a little,
but maybe
there is an opening.
Yes, and I understand
the importance of having the majority,
but at
the same time, risk is central in this game.
And someone will be fifth
in this alliance.
And this person
will not reach the top alone.
Lindsey, the danger for you
is that LJ and Jefra
have nothing to lose.
It's true. I mean...
I hate to say that,
but I think
we should stick together.
I think we have a better
chance, because it's not 5-2,
it will be us five,
and then the other tribe,
ultimately together.
Without Jefra and LJ.
Cliff, is there anything
cathartic about finally coming here?
I see it as
the NBA playoffs.
The season only really starts
when you lose a game.
The old Aparri,
we hadn't been here yet.
We really do not know
what goes on in
one or the other's head.
Once we see it,
we can make adjustments
and go ahead.
Do you dread, Tony,
that tonight's advice
could tilt the game
one way or the other?
This advice will definitely swing
the game one way or the other.
After tonight's vote,
we will see
if we can move
forward as a team,
or if we're going
to take a step back
and move forward
with a different team.
It all depends on the outcome of the vote.
Well, it's time to vote.
Woo, it's up to you.
Sorry, buddy.
The last thing we need
is for you to reach fusion
and reform
the Beauty Tribe.
Cliff, you can't
decide everything forever.
I hope the others
will follow the plan.
Nothing personal,
it's purely strategic.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote.
LJ.
Cliff. Equality.
Two Cliff votes, two LJ votes.
That's three LJ votes,
two Cliff votes.
Cliff. Equality.
Three Cliff votes, three LJ votes.
One vote remains.
Fifth person eliminated
from Survivor Cagayan:
Cliff. You must
bring me your torch.
Cliff, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck to you.
It's time to go.
It worked.
Oh my God.
You came to the board
with a big question.
Where does the loyalty lie
in this group?
I believe you have the answer.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
Trish makes me sick.
- A bitter quarrel...
- Lindsey isn't helping.
- ...has been growing for days.
- I can not stand her.
And can no longer be contained.
Everything you are,
I can't stand it.
I don't love you.
She is tyrannical,
I can't stand her presence.
What's going on?
I had too much faith
in my alliance.
I thought I was...
aware of
what was happening in the camp.
But it's hard, it's hard.
And that's what happens in this game.
When you think
things are going your way
boom, you're being betrayed.