translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
18 new castaways
were divided into three tribes:
Muscle, Intelligence and Beauty.
Welcome to Survivor Cagayan.
In the Beauty tribe,
LJ was suspicious of Morgan.
Either she already has the idol,
or she has a clue.
While Morgan suspected
that Brice and her
had against them
a covenant of four:
LJ and Jeremiah
and Alexis and Jefra.
Brice and I, we stick together.
He protects me.
They tried
to recruit Jeremiah.
We country
people have to stick together.
Meanwhile, in the Muscle tribe,
Tony was going at top speed,
finding an idol...
That's huge.
... et manipulant sa tribe.
- Are you a cop?
- No why?
- Do you swear?
- I swear.
I wondered for a moment
if I should tell him I'm a cop.
But if I say so, they'll try
to take me out by surprise right away.
Immunity test...
The Muscle Tribe wins!
...The Intelligence tribe
continued to self-destruct.
J'Tia is starting to panic!
Beauty wins!
Squandering their huge lead,
they lost their second race in a row.
Back at camp,
things got worse.
Garrett decided
to hold a public vote.
Kass, do you have an opinion?
J'Tia.
But it didn't have the desired effect.
Garrett, you are an idiot!
At the council, the women decided
that strategy
was more important than eating.
They eliminated Garrett,
leaving Spencer alone.
Garrett, the tribe has spoken.
Who wants to
welcome me to the bottom of the tribe?
Sixteen remain.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
I didn't see it coming.
The advice was a disaster.
Garrett has been bad enough
so that the girls prefer
the one that destroyed all our food.
Which is crazy.
I am clearly alone against all.
I'm gonna need all kinds
of crazy ideas to stand a chance.
If he hadn't organized
his mock council...
It would have been J'Tia,
if we could have talked in private.
Yeah.
I arrived at the council
thinking of leaving.
But I had a lot of luck,
a lot of Kass.
This tribe is a disaster,
but it's entertaining.
We'll see what happens.
I was going to vote for J'Tia,
I was serious saying it.
When did you change your mind?
When I found out
you and Kass Garrett had an alliance.
Yeah...
I'm still mad
at the rice, mad at J'Tia,
but I have no agreement with Spencer.
I will do my best to
drag Kass into an alliance of girls.
Spencer is not going to stop there.
- He's the next to go.
- Yes, I was thinking about that.
He's the next to go.
- Let's do this between girls.
- Let's go.
When I got to the council,
I didn't know who to vote for.
But Garrett, he's fun
to watch, but not to play.
"J'Tia has her character",
but rice can be replaced,
and now she is afraid.
Then I think she will be loyal to me.
I hope you wo
n't prefer Spencer to me.
- Because I...
- Damn, no!
Damn no!
I do not trust anyone.
They are against me.
It's me, myself, my idol,
and me again. We are four.
But I was alone by the fire,
and Sarah arrived.
"Let's give him
something and see."
I've been a cop in a big city
for thirteen years.
"Listen, Sara".
"I'm also a cop,
you were right."
How did you know?
I can see it.
I've been a cop for seven years..
My wife has been a cop for eight years.
Damn, I knew it, man.
I say. No problem.
Some say cops
spot each other like gays.
I know how to recognize a cop.
And Tony is a cop.
I knew it from day one.
And he finally told me.
I thought I won the lottery.
"Damn it! I knew it!"
Can you imagine what we could do?
Can you imagine
two cops...? Cops'R'Us!
Now that I know he is a cop,
the solidarity of the "blues" plays.
The cops stick together.
He will be loyal.
And I'll be by his side, believe it.
We'll do the 400 shots together.
It's Cliff and Lindsey.
They wanted to take out Trish,
but then it was you,
because you are too smart.
I told Sarah about a conversation
between Cliff and Lindsey,
but it was a pure lie.
I just told him that
to lure him to my side.
It's us against the rest of the world.
- On my badge.
- OK.
To me, that means nothing.
You can swear on your children,
your family, your dead grandmother...
Doesn't matter. It's just words.
I never trust anyone.
Me neither, at this point.
And you shouldn't.
It's not true, this rain!
Come on!
It really sucks.
It's really rough.
This weather is
the worst experience of my life.
It's the monsoon, or a hurricane.
Everything is soggy.
I'm desperately trying
to preserve that little spark.
But everything is soaked.
Basically, we're screwed.
Miserables. Completely miserable.
It's rough.
I'm kidding,
but it's not funny.
You know what they say, huh?
The sun always rises in the morning.
Look at the water!
Look at this!
There are others?
This rain is treacherous, treacherous,
freezing, torrential.
But that's it, Survivor!
Hopefully
it will calm down soon.
Otherwise, the night will be long.
Drink some water, kid.
Oh, that's good, Woo.
I haven't been dry for more than
two hours straight on this island.
It's raining nonstop.
It's tough on morale.
We are all miserable.
That's how I imagine hell.
If only
we had won this tarp!
We've been up all night.
Since sunset,
we are there to snuggle up.
I think my fingernail is broken.
He must have fallen
because he's soggy.
This is the
most ridiculous situation I have ever known.
And I would have preferred to avoid it.
I don't sympathize with Lindsey,
because last night
I spoke with Tony,
and he informed me that Cliff
and Lindsey had talked about me,
which immediately
pissed me off.
- Tell me.
- This is what I heard:
"We can eliminate Trish
whenever we want."
"When we want."
"It's Sarah, the smart one."
That's what they said.
"I like Sarah."
"It's a game,
you have to stay focused."
That's what he said.
I'm telling you.
Police solidarity, mate.
We formed Cops'R'Us last night.
- Cops'R'Us.
- But be serious.
- If you panic...
- It won't happen.
That's why
I wanted to talk to you.
I had to find you, Tony.
If you betray your word,
it's Survivor, that's one thing.
But if you say "police solidarity"
and then betray me...
No. That's why I said that.
- OK?
- Absolutely.
He knows that I will be loyal,
and vice versa.
We shook hands again.
There couldn't be
a more sincere handshake.
I trust him 110%.
When you finally told me,
- "I knew it!".
OK see you.
Whatever you tell someone,
you can't trust them.
I don't trust anyone
here, anyone.
None of them.
And I'm sure it's mutual.
If it could stop,
just ten minutes...
Just enough to take
a turn and take a breather.
What do these flies have?
They adore us!
I feel like I'm
in a Survivor nightmare.
It's horrible. Last night
we had a terrible storm.
Our clothes are soaked.
They won't dry out today.
Our fingers, see,
are completely...
We've been in the water
for almost 24 hours.
We haven't slept.
We didn't eat anything at all,
no way to make a fire.
Reality takes over.
It's really very hard.
Do you think we should
strip down and go in the water?
I'm afraid of being even colder.
We need another plan
for tonight, otherwise it won't work.
Unfortunately, Jefra
complains a lot but does little.
I know what that means.
"Jeremiah and LJ, prepare the shelter!"
You have to work hard to
get out of it in a survival situation.
And the beauty stereotype is
starting to apply.
These girls do nothing.
They are on another planet.
- It's not so bad.
- Yeah, it looks drier.
It's definitely drier.
You have to put palm leaves on it.
Otherwise it won't hold.
This is one of those situations
where I have to shut up.
To not become a target.
I had never seen the monsoon.
There, I am in the first row.
I'm frozen.
We're wet, soggy,
we're not about to dry out,
and my mind is constantly active.
I thought on day 1,
when I knocked out Morgan,
we arrived at the camp
and she arrived from the reef.
That she was there for no reason...
She must have had a clue.
So I said to myself that I was going to
see if I didn't find an idol there.
Who would look for
an idol in the middle of a hurricane?
This guy! That's why
I found it.
I have the immunity idol.
I was taught that hard work pays off.
We reap what we sow.
Now I have an ace in the game.
It does not have a price.
Now I have
to find a hiding place for him.
I keep it to myself,
no one will know that I have it
before I play it.
- Tree mail.
- Our favorite place.
There is mail.
- A small...
- Character.
Something positive, please!
We have a small character.
Like a Buddha.
Maybe a meditation test.
The one who meditates the longest.
- Who wants to read?
- Me.
"You will be misled and lost.
That's for sure."
Un labyrinth.
"In this ordeal,
the tribe works together,
throwing little
buckets of water from the ocean
in a bigger bucket,
at the end of a seesaw beam.
Gaining immunity is also
gaining drier shelter."
A tarp.
I need rice.
I really want rice.
Yes, let's cook some.
- I have to eat something.
- And water.
J'Tia threw away 95% of our rice,
but she asks how much to cook.
"You're kidding?".
It is ironical.
It's a mess here.
A trial awaits us,
someone might leave,
and my first idea,
- "let's practice".
Let's hurry.
I would like us to train
different techniques.
I'm going to do some
interior decorating.
Sorry, I'm really dehydrated.
Priorities are wrong.
And people look at me like
I'm the crazy one.
You should really
want us to practice.
Really.
- You know what I mean.
- I want us to be good, yes.
If we lose, someone leaves.
Drinking is also essential.
It's weird being the only man.
I have to be patient,
manage my emotions, keep my spirits up,
and I must try to come out
of this tribe alive.
The problem
is that it disperses.
Like that? Nope?
I think you have to
give it a shot.
What I did was perfect.
Non.
A little high.
Lower I can handle.
In height, I do not like.
The jet should not
be too high.
Not in the face.
Fix my coco.
So. You have to have a target.
I like the technique of the hand.
Yes exactly.
Oui!
Over here, everyone!
Muscle and Beauty, discover
the new Intelligence tribe.
Garrett was eliminated
at the last council.
Again,
shocked reactions.
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all,
I take back the idols.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will draw
water from the ocean with a bucket,
then you will pass it
between team members to a container.
When it is full,
it will release a ball.
Two team members will use it
to solve a vertical maze.
The first two tribes to finish...
gain immunity,
are shielded from the vote.
The losers go to the council,
where a third person
will be eliminated from Survivor Cagayan.
You are also playing for a reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
Considering the weather, it will help you a lot.
Comfort and protection.
Oh my God!
Blankets, pillows, mosquito net,
and a tarp to stay dry.
Whatever the state of your shelter,
a tarp will improve it.
For the second tribe...
No comfort, but
the protection of a tarpaulin.
A lot at stake in this event.
Muscle, you have two
more limbs. Who will not participate?
Lindsey and me?
Jeff, Lindsey and me.
Tony and Lindsey do
not participate in the Muscle Tribe.
Tribu Beauté, two people
will not participate. Which?
- Me, Jeff.
- And me.
Jefra and Alexis.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, one minute to
get organized, and we'll begin.
Let's go!
For immunity and reward!
Survivors, ready?
Teamwork is the key.
Attractive!
First throw the bucket,
then throw the water.
Whatever comes to you,
you have to pour it out.
You need to collect as much
water as possible in each round.
Once the container is full,
the ball will be released,
and this step will be completed!
Kass, not much in the bucket!
From the start, Beauty leads.
Muscle is right behind.
Intelligence is last,
as usual.
Spencer desperately tries
to change things.
He goes as fast as he can,
to Tasha, then to J'Tia.
Who is soggy!
Very little water reaches Kass!
The Beauty tribe stands out.
Whatever they do, it works.
Awesome throw from the Muscle Tribe!
But throw!
Tasha and J'Tia still have
trouble communicating.
Beauty is about
to finish this first step.
Muscle is second,
Intelligence always last.
There is advice tonight,
you have to speed up!
Beauty is very close.
Morgan touches it.
That might be enough.
Let's go!
It's good for the Beauty Tribe!
Start the maze!
The second place is played
between Muscle and Intelligence.
Beauty works on the maze.
Shoot first!
Cliff has another bucket of water,
and that'll be enough for Muscle!
Go for it! Start the maze!
Don't give up, Intelligence!
- Left or right?
- Not important.
Two tribes are
on the vertical maze.
The Muscle tribe and the Beauty tribe.
Once again, Intelligence
tries to get back into the ordeal.
They are far enough away.
As soon as she goes down,
I pull on my side.
You have to coordinate
to get the ball out,
until she falls.
Intelligence
still hasn't won.
Once again, no water
in J'Tia's bucket for Kass.
Slight advance of Muscle
in the maze.
But Beauty is just behind.
You just have to make sure you
don't finish last!
That's enough!
Intelligence attacks the maze.
A new opportunity
to earn their name!
But Muscle and Beauty had
plenty of time to move on,
and to understand
a complicated maze.
Muscle is getting closer.
They understood!
They are one move
away from victory!
Here we are! That might be enough!
Muscle gains immunity
and reward!
There is still a place!
Intelligence is back!
Start again!
They collaborate well for
the first time in this event!
Another big move
for the Intelligence Tribe!
Beauty is now in trouble!
Intelligence has never been
so close to completion.
They would come a long way.
The Beauty Tribe is falling apart!
Intelligence is almost there!
Big move for Intelligence!
That should do!
Intelligence wins immunity
and reward!
No advice, for
the first time this season!
Oh my God!
Muscle tribe, congratulations.
Immunity, again!
No advice,
and a nice reward.
Tribu Intelligence,
you've been waiting a while.
Taste immunity!
It is deserved.
And there's a tarp with it.
Muscle, come get
your reward.
Enjoy a new evening
without advice.
Intelligence, come and get
your tarp, go back to camp.
- I will miss you on the council.
- We won't miss you.
Beauty, I have nothing for you,
except an appointment with me
tonight at the council,
where someone will be
the third person eliminated.
Take your things, return
to camp. See you at the council.
Our dear home!
Look at this mess.
See you later, palm leaf!
We tore it all up again.
We all know how to keep
our cool under pressure.
It will be waterproof.
We have the cover, we have the comfort.
That's crazy.
I feel alive again.
Let it come, the rain!
Let's set up the hammock!
When we brought back
the elements of comfort,
I thought to myself that there was perhaps
a clue or an advantage in it.
My brain is spinning
and theirs aren't, I guess.
I don't know what happens to them.
But I immediately thought
that I had to grab everything.
I took the hammock out of the way,
in case something fell.
I open it, and a piece of paper
resembling a clue falls out.
I put my foot on it.
I look, there is no one.
I pick it up
and put it in my pocket.
It's not that I need it,
I already have the idol.
But I wanted to make sure
that if there was something,
a clue, an advantage,
I put my hand on it,
that no one else sees it.
That's what I did.
That's great!
Oh my God.
The first element of comfort.
Does anyone mind
if I go in the hammock?
I hope you fall on your ass.
I just wanted to sit there!
Dreams come true in Survivor!
Sorry.
We win as a team, we lose as a team.
You have assured with water.
Nice job, Morgan.
Oh my God.
You had such a lead...
I hate
making excuses for myself, so...
We did not succeed.
Here, we are confronted
with a lot of elements at the same time.
Stay alive!
We're in the middle of a hurricane.
We lost the race.
We are exhausted.
And now we're going to the council.
The atmosphere on our camp
will become very dark.
It will fill
with negativity and suspicion.
A silly question...
Anyone want to leave?
It's stupid, but in case
anyone gets bored...
Might as well ask the question.
Tonight, we're finally going to the council.
It had to happen eventually.
Jeremiah, me, Alexis and Jefra
are on the same wavelength.
Between Morgan and Brice,
only Brice worries me.
He looks like the guy
who will be formidable at the end of the game.
It is better to act
against Brice now.
It will be Bruce.
If anything happens,
it will be Brice.
I think, yeah.
I'm afraid the tribe
agrees
that I am not
physically dangerous,
but that I am socially.
They might target me,
but I trust Jeremiah.
I just want to make sure we're
okay with eliminating a girl.
What do you really think?
I'm thinking of Alexis, but...
Did LJ talk to you?
Not really, he thinks...
He thinks of you.
If it's me, he'll target you next.
I do not know.
Don't try to convince him.
Are you up for voting Alexis?
Then we should stick together
and vote Alexis.
OK.
LJ believes he is allied
with Alexis, Jefra, Jeremiah.
But in reality,
Jeremiah is with Brice and me.
I didn't think I was
going to council tonight.
It sucks.
We need to talk to him.
For tonight, we are trying
to recruit Jefra, to make it 4-2.
What's new?
We want you to vote Alexis with us.
I know you two are
good friends, but...
Why not eliminate LJ instead?
We need him for the tests.
Jeremiah is coming to talk to you.
When did you speak with Jeremiah?
The last days.
And he's leaving?
LJ thinks Jeremiah
is in his alliance.
Morgan, Jeremiah and Brice are allies.
They're going to vote Alexis tonight.
What's going on?
Is Jeremiah
with Alexis, LJ and me?
Or with Brice and Morgan?
I do not know.
That's what we said...
I may have the opportunity
to speak with Jeremiah.
He will come talk to you.
People are throwing out strategies
that I didn't know anything about.
It's totally crazy.
This advice does not excite me,
because someone is going to have a surprise.
Morgan came to say
crazy things to me.
- What did she say?
- That you are allied with Brice and her.
And that Brice, she and you
are going to vote Alexis.
- Don't.
- OK.
- So the plan holds?
- Yes.
- You, me, LJ and...
- Alexis.
You, me, LJ and Alexis,
we vote for Brice.
- Are we still okay?
- Yes.
Jefra does not want to vote against Alexis.
Brice and Morgan are going to vote Alexis.
So... I'm stuck.
Share the votes?
Is there a risk?
I do not think so. If we tie 2-2,
and they have 2 against someone...
- There will be a tie.
- And we'll vote again.
And then, if no
one leaves an idol, we all vote for Brice.
I don't believe there is
any risk in sharing.
So who...
The boys vote for Brice,
the girls vote for Morgan.
Brice or Morgan
could have an idol,
so we're going to split the votes.
The two boys will vote Morgan,
the two girls will vote Brice.
If neither of
them leaves an idol, we will vote again,
and we will all vote for Brice.
Are you sure that can't
get one of us out?
There is always the fear
that an idol will be played.
If I get my majority to split
their votes, there will be a tie.
And I will be in the center.
We share.
The boys for Morgan,
the girls for Brice.
We can do that.
If I go with Brice and Morgan,
I can eliminate Alexis.
My main goal
is to control the tribe.
Above all, I hope to become a majority.
Be sure to vote Alexis,
please.
I'm not worried,
I trust Jeremiah and Morgan.
It sucks.
Our first tip...
I don't know what to expect.
Jefra seems much more comfortable
with Jeremiah than with LJ.
Our alliance will be revealed,
everyone will know their position.
I have a big decision to make.
I can go with LJ, Alexis
and Jefra, or with Brice and Morgan.
Going to the council with all
the power is an incredible feeling.
But I'm just a country boy,
I don't want to hurt anyone.
And with this vote,
it might be.
Some will lose their confidence,
this is probably
what will hurt me the most.
Behind you, torches.
Take one,
bring it close to the fire and light it.
It's part of
the tribal council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
When your fire goes out,
it's the end for you.
Morgan, let's talk about you being
made into the Beauty Tribe.
Does this tribe embody
some of the clichés about beauty?
Yes, we have beautiful faces.
What can I say? I like it.
Sorry.
A bug in my hair.
Brice, how did you feel
being placed in the Beauty tribe?
I was excited.
I see myself as a handsome guy.
It goes with inner strength,
and life experience,
to have this butterfly effect,
where the caterpillar becomes a butterfly.
I'm in the butterfly stage of my life,
I'm flying and I'm beautiful.
Jefra, tell me
about the first days here.
The first few days
were a bit of a party, Jeff.
We were like friends
at university, all beautiful, having fun.
Then the storm came,
and the general attitude changed.
We lost the race today,
and everyone is paranoid.
Because until now, to my knowledge,
no one had talked about strategy.
Brice, did you feel
that paranoia this afternoon?
Everyone is worried tonight,
but there have been discussions.
Groups formed.
Jeremiah and LJ are together.
Alexis and Jefra are together.
Sometimes the four of them are together,
and Morgan and I are apart.
If you and Morgan are apart,
are you worried?
There are a lot of discussions.
But some didn't
discuss strategy with me at all.
Who?
Alexis didn't tell me at all
about alliances or the game.
So I'm pretty sure
she's going to vote against me.
Can we deduce
that you will vote Alexis?
Jeff, I think everyone
should do their part at camp.
- Three little dots?
- Three little dots!
Alexis, what do you think?
Are you doing your part?
He knows the game, he can
use that to get me out.
I love Brice,
and being in his company.
I hope that's not the case,
but it could happen.
Brice, have we wondered
about the presence of idols?
We discussed it, someone
might have an idol.
For example Morgan, since
she was the first on the camp.
I know that the
possible presence of idols has been discussed.
Morgan, all this
idol talk,
What do you think?
I'm a little worried, of course.
I think I know where things are going,
if all goes as planned.
But you can always
be betrayed without seeing it coming.
Jeremiah, we've established
that Brice, Morgan and Alexis
are all a little worried.
Do you think you know
what will happen?
It will be hard.
I think I know what will happen,
but it will be painful.
But this is Survivor.
There seems to be
a lot of uncertainty.
Let's end it.
It's time to vote.
Morgan, it's up to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote.
One vote Alexis,
one vote Brice, one vote Morgan.
Alexis.
That's two votes Alexis.
Brice.
Two Brice votes, two Alexis votes,
one Morgan vote, one vote remains.
Morgan.
Equality.
Alexis, Morgan and Brice,
you won't vote.
LJ, Jefra and Jeremiah,
you will vote again,
only for one of these three.
LJ, it's up to you. Come take this.
I will count the votes.
I will read the votes.
First vote...
Brice.
Third person eliminated
from Survivor Cagayan...
Brice.
That's two, that's enough.
Bring me your torch.
Brice, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
With this first defeat
and this first elimination,
you got your first taste
of how this game really plays.
How long
will it take for you to recover?
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
We could easily
lose on purpose.
The Muscle Tribe plans
to betray one of their own.
Let's lose the trial and eliminate him.
And an ordeal leaves
no one unscathed.
It will leave a mark!
I'm a little mad at Jeremiah.
He betrayed me, but that's okay.
I'm sure he does
n't really understand what happened.
I'm surprised
he can spell my name.
They clearly wanted
get rid of
the prettiest, the best dressed first.
I am happy to have this title,
under the vivas.
I hope Morgan does
well.
As for the others,
I have forgotten their names.