>> Jeff: WELCOME, EVERYONE, TO
THE TWO-HOUR FINALE OF
"SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN" BRAINS
VERSUS BRAWN VERSUS BEAUTY.
WE ARE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
FULL OF "SURVIVOR" FANS.
IT'S A TOUGH TICKET TO GET.
CLEARLY THEY'RE AMPED UP.
AND I KNOW YOU GUYS ARE, TOO.
IT IS A VERY EXCITING NIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO BE LIVE
THROUGHOUT THE TWO-HOUR FINALE.
AND THEN WE HAVE THE LIVE
REUNION SHOW.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOOD.
YOU EARNED YOUR KEEP.
YOU EARNED YOUR TICKETS.
AND THEN WE HAVE THE THE REUNION
SHOW WHERE WE WILL BRING BACK
ALL OF THE PLAYERS AND REHASH
WHAT WENT DOWN AND THERE'S
DEFINITELY A LOT TO TALK ABOUT
FROM THIS VERY GOOD SEASON.
YOU CAN SHARE YOUR THOUGHTS
ABOUT THE SEASON AND THE
FINALE@JEFFPROBATE ON TWITTER.
THIS IS MY LIVING ROOM FOR
TONIGHT, TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I HOPE YOU SETTLE INTO YOURS,
LAY OUT YOUR SNACKS, PUT YOUR
FEET UP, CALL YOUR FRIENDS, AND
GET READY FOR A NIGHT TO VOTE TO
YOUR FAVORITE SHOW "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR" IS THE
BIGGEST SOCIAL EXPERIMENT ON
TELEVISION, AND THIS SEASON, IT
WAS TAKEN TO ANOTHER LEVEL.
18 CASTAWAYS WERE DIVIDED
INTO
THREE TRIBES BASED ON THE
PERSONALITY TRAITS THEY USED
MOST IN THEIR DAILY LIVES.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: BRAWN.
>> WE'RE GOING TO STOMP ON
BEAUTY AND WE'RE GOING TO STOMP
ON SMART.
>> Jeff: BRAINS.
>> I GUESS WE'RE THE NERDS.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: AND BEAUTY.
>> I THINK WE'RE BEAUTY.
>> Jeff: THE ONLY QUESTION WAS
WHICH QUALITY WOULD PROVE THE
MOST VALUABLE.
THE BRAWN TRIBE QUICKLY LIVED UP
TO THEIR NAME.
PUTTING THEIR MUSCLES TO GOOD
USE AND BUILDING A STRONG TRIBE.
>> I COULD TELL THAT WE'RE
DEFINITELY GOING TO DOMINATE.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: THE BEAUTY TRIBE
THRIVED AS WELL.
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> FIRE!
>> Jeff: TURNING A TOUGH GAME
INTO A VIRTUAL VACATION.
>> I'M LOVIN' 'OUR TRIBE.
YOU GUYS ARE THE BOMB.
>> Jeff: BUT THE BRAIN TRIBE
WAS A DIFFERENT STORY.
>> NO, NO, NO, FLAT SIDE.
>> Jeff: THEY OVERTHOUGHT
EVERYTHING.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE FOUR
STAKES, THREE FEET HIGH.
>> Jeff: AND IT WAS A
DISASTER.
>> NOT VERY SMART FOR THE BRAIN
TRIBE.
>> Jeff: THEY WERE ONE OF THE
WORST TRIBES IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY.
THEY COULDN'T GET ALONG--
>> SOUND LIKE THE MENTAL
PATIENT.
YOU LEFT THE MENTAL PATIENT
ALONE AND I WENT CRAZY.
>> Jeff: AND THEY COULDN'T WIN
A CHALLENGE.
THERE IT IS, BRAWN WINS, SENDING
THE BRAIN TRIBE TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL ONCE AGAIN.
>> HOW DID WE COME UP WITH THE
CRITERIA FOR BRAINS?
I'D LIKE TO SEE THAT DATA.
>> Jeff: FORTUNATELY FOR THEM,
THERE WAS A TWIST IN THE GAME.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY, DROP YOUR
BUFFS.
WE'RE GOING TO FORM TWO NEW
TRIBES.
AFTER THE SWITCH, THE THREE
REMAINING BRAIN MEMBERS WERE ALL
ON THE NEW APARRI TRIBE WHERE
THEY FOUND THEMSELVES ON THE TOP
THE FOOD CHAIN.
OVER ON THE NEW SOLANA TRIBE.
>> MAN, LOOK AT THE SHELTER.
>> Jeff: BRAWN HAD A 5-2
ADVANTAGE OVER L.J. AND JEFRA.
BUT MATH WAS NEVER THEIR STRONG
SUIT.
>> I WANT TO GET CLIFF OUT.
>> HEY, LET'S POUND ON IT, ALL
RIGHT.
>> Jeff: AND THEY BEGAN TO
TURN ON EACH OTHER.
>> I DON'T LIKE CLIFF.
CLIFF IS A VERY INFLUENTIAL
PERSON.
>> Jeff: FIFTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF "SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN,"
CLIFF.
CLIFF WAS BLINDSIDED IN A
SHOCKING VOTE.
AND WHEN THEY COULDN'T GET ALONG
--
>> EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU I CANNOT
STAND.
>> LET ME MAKE THIS REALLY CLEAR
TO YOU-- I DON'T LIKE YOU.
>> Jeff: LINDSEY JUST PLAIN
QUIT.
LINDY IS PULLING HERSELF FROM
THE GAME.
>> SHE WAS THE BODY, CLIFS WAS
THE HEAD.
TWO FOR THE PRICE OF ONE.
>> IS THAT A ROW BOAT?
>> I THINK SOMETHING'S BREWING.
>> Jeff: WHEN THE TRIBES
MERGED--
>> WE COME IN PEACE!
>> Jeff: THE DIVISION OF POWER
WAS CLEAR.
>> THERE IS A GROUP OF FIVE,
WHICH IS MY ALLIANCE, AND A
GROUP OF SIX HALF BRAIN, AND
HALF BEAUTY, AND THEN YOU HAVE
SARAH.
>> I WILL DECIDE THE FATE OF
THIS GAME.
>> ANOTHER IDOL WITH DIFFERENT
POWERS IS HIDDEN SOMEWHERE NEAR
YOUR CAMP.
>> Jeff: AND A NEW IDOL WITH
DIFFERENT POWERS WAS PUT IN
PLAY.
>> IT WAS POWERFUL ENOUGH ON ITS
OWN AND NOW IT'S SPECIAL POWERS.
>> Jeff: BUT THE FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL AFTER THE MERGE TURNED
OUT TO BE A DEFINING MOMENT.
MULTIPLE IDOL WERE PLAYED--
>> I'D LIKE TO GIVE IT TO L.J.
>> HOLD ON, JEFF.
>> Jeff: YES.
>> I'D LIKE TO COVER TONY'S ASS
MYSELF.
>> Jeff: THIS IS ALSO A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
KASS FLIPPED ON HER ALLIANCE,
AND THE MOST COMFORT TRIBEMEMBER
WAS BLINDSIDED.
>> KASS, ZERO CHANCE OF WINNING
GAME.
>> Jeff: FROM THAT POINT ON,
THERE WAS ONLY ONE RULE FOR
"SURVIVOR: CAGAYAN--" PLAY HARD
OR GO HOME.
THERE WERE THINGS WE'VE NEVER
SEEN BEFORE--
>> IT'S A RACE.
>> Jeff: BATTLES FOR HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOLS.
>> YOU HAVE TWO DIFFERENT
ALLIANCES LOOKING FOR AN IDOL AT
THE SAME TIME.
>> Jeff: DRAWING ROCKS FOR AN
ADVANTAGE.
TONY DRAWS THE ADVANTAGE.
>> WHOO!
>> I'M THE GREATEST LOSENER
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
>> Jeff: AND EVEN A SPY SHACK.
>> BING!
>> Jeff: THERE WERE ALSO
IMMUNITY RUNS.
TASHA WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
SUPERPOWER SHE DOES IT, TASHA
WINS IMMUNITY.
TASHA WINS.
BLUNDERS.
>> COME ON DOWN, BROTHER.
>> Jeff: IDOL FINDS.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I HAVE TWO IDOLS.
EVEN THE SPECIAL IDOL.
>> Jeff: AND GOOD
OLD-FASHIONED BLINDSIDES.
L.J.
JEFRA.
WHEN ALL THE DUST SETTLED, TWO
BRAIN AND THREE BRAWN REMAINED,
AND THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS
NO DIFFERENT THAN THE REST.
WOW, BIG REACTION.
TONY BLUFFED ABOUT HIS POWERLESS
IDOL THAT HE'S HOPING WILL BE
HIS TICKET TO THE END.
>> FIVE PEOPLE LEFT.
I HAVE TO USE IT, AND I HAVE
ANOTHER SURPRISE FOR THEM WHEN I
USE THIS IDOL, JEFF, BUT I WON'T
DISCLOSE THAT YET AS OF NOW.
>> Jeff: TRISH.
>> IT WAS ANOTHER DEVASTATING
BLINDSIDE.
>> Jeff: TRISH, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU, GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: AND SPENCER WAS LEFT
AT THE BOTTOM ONCE AGAIN.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU HAVE MADE
IT TO THE FINAL FOUR, AND MY
PREDICTION IS IT IS GOING TO BE
A WILD FINISH.
POWER ARE LEFT.
TONY-- THIS NEW JERSEY COP WILL
STOP AT NOTHING TO WIN THE GAME.
HE'S FOUND THREE IMMUNITY IDOLS
AND HAS OH, STRAIGHT MULTIPLE
BLINDSIDES.
WILL HIS AGGRESSIVE GAME GET HIM
TO THE END OR WILL IT BACKFIRE?
>> I'M PROBABLY THE VILLAIN, BUT
EVERYTHING I DID WAS SURVIVAL
BASED.
I CAME TO WIN A MILLION DOLLARS,
AND MY FOCUS IS STILL TO WIN A
MILLION DOLLARS.
>> Jeff: WOO-- THIS MARTIAL
ARTS INSTRUCTOR IS A SOCIAL AND
PHYSICAL THREAT.
BUT TO GET TO THE END, IT WILL
TAKE SOMETHING DIFFERENT FROM
WITHIN.
>> BEING ABLE TO ADAPT IS VERY
CRITICAL.
YOU PUT WATER INTO A BOWL, YOU
GOTTA BECOME BOWL.
IF I CONTINUE TO DO THAT, THEN I
HAVE A GREAT SHOT AT COMING OUT
ON TOP.
>> Jeff: KASS.
SHE NICKNAMED HERSELF "CHAOS
KASS" AND IT WASN'T FAR FROM THE
TRUTH.
SHE HAS BEEN THE CENTER OF
CONFLICT, AND NEVER AFRAID TO
CHANGE THE GAME.
SHE'LL TAKE DOWN ANYONE WHO
STANDS IN HER WAY.
>> THIS IS A GAME.
I'M NOT YOUR FRIEND.
I'M NOT HERE TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
I MEAN, IT'S "SURVIVOR."
NO ONE HAS INTEGRITY.
IT'S A MILLION BUCKS.
>> Jeff: SPENCER-- HIS GAME
HAS BEEN ONE WILD RIDE.
HE'S GONE FROM TOP TO BOTTOM
MORE THAN ANY OTHER SURVIVOR.
BUT THROUGH IT ALL, HE HAS NEVER
GIVEN UP.
WILL THIS UNDERDOG FINALLY CATCH
A BREAK?
>> I HAVE TO GO INTO THIS OUT
FOR BLOOD, READY TO WIN AT ALL
COSTS BECAUSE THIS IS IT.
THIS IS MY SHOT AT THE MILLION
DOLLARS RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
>> Jeff: FIND OUT TONIGHT WHO
WILL WIN THE MILLION DOLLAR
PRIZE AND TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> NICE TRIBAL, GUYS.
THAT'S ONE FOR THE BOOKS.
THAT WAS CRAZY.
WAIT, SO, TONY, YOU VOTED FOR
TRISH?
>> YEAH.
>> WHY DID YOU VOTE FOR TRISH?
>> BECAUSE I DON'T PLAY THE GAME
ON EMOTIONS, KASS.
I PLAY IT STRATEGICALLY.
>> DID YOU TALK TO WOO ABOUT THE
FACT YOU WERE GOING TO DO THAT?
>> AND I DO NOT FEEL GOOD ABOUT
IT AT ALL.
SHE HASN'T HURT NOBODY.
SHE HASN'T BLINDSIDED ANYBODY.
SHE HASN'T DONE ANYTHING FOR
ANYBODY TO DISLIKE, AND YOU
CAN'T TAKE SOMEBODY LIKE THAT TO
THE END.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
I'M A LITTLE SAD THAT I HAD TO
OUST ONE OF MY BEST ALLIES, ONE
OF MY MOST LOYAL, MOST HONEST,
MOST SINCERE ALLIES WHICH WAS
TRISH.
BUT I HAD NO CHOICE.
AND I FEEL HORRIBLE ABOUT IT,
BUT I THINK IT WAS THE MOST
STRATEGIC MOVE FOR ME TO MAKE.
>> CONGRATS, GUYS.
>> CONGRATS, SPENCE, MAN.
>> CONGRATS, KASS.
>> FINAL FOUR, THAT'S AWESOME.
>> CONGRATS, EVERYONE.
>> IT'S A BEAUTIFUL THING, MAN.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M AT THE
FINAL FOUR.
I MEAN GETTING THROWN UNDER THE
BUS TIME AFTER TIME AFTER TIME.
I'M AMAZED THAT I'M HERE.
BUT TRIBAL WAS DEMORALIZING WHEN
TONY PULLED OUT HIS SECOND IDOL
THAT LOOKED SIMILAR TO THE
NORMAL IDOL THAT WAS HEAVIER AND
TIED AROUND A STRING.
>> THE SAME THING, AS YOU KNOW,
THAT IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE A
NECKLACE, YOU CAN'T GO TO THE
FINALS BECAUSE YOU'RE A THREAT.
>> RIGHT.
>> SAME THING AS ME.
I KNOW IF I DIDN'T HAVE
PROTECTION, I WASN'T GOING TO
THE FINALS.
I'M GUARANTEED FINAL THREE SO
IT'S UP TO ME PRETTY MUCH.
>> SOMEONE COULD WIN IMMUNITY.
>> FENDING ON WHAT THE POWERS
ARE.
THAT I'M NOT GOING TO DISCUSS IT
ANY FURTHER.
>> IF TONY IS ACTUALLY
GUARANTEED THE FINAL THREE, LIKE
HE CLAIMS, IT'S GOING TO MEAN
PROBLEMS FOR ME.
WE'VE BEEN ARCH RIVALS THE
ENTIRE GAME, AND IF HE MAKES IT
TO THE END, IT CAN BE GOOD FOR
MY GAME.
>> POTENTIALLY WHO YOU WINS.
>> THE VOTE WILL BE 3-1 OR 2-2
FOR THE OTHER TWO, AND I DON'T
KNOW HOW TONY'S IDOL FIGURES
INTO ALL OF THAT.
WE'LL SEE.
>> WE WILL SEE, MAN.
BACK HOME, ON MY MOTHERLAND, I'M
A POLICE OFFICER, I CAN'T BE
CORRUPT.
OUT HERE ALL I'M DOING IS
BLUFFING AND I'M LYING MY ASS
OFF.
>> KASS, HOW SHOCKED WERE WERE
YOU WHEN HE PULLED THAT OUT.
>> I WAS SURPRISED HE HAD IT.
>> I HAVE BEEN TELLING THEM
ABOUT THE IDOL, AND I'VE BEEN
BLUFFING SAYING I CAN USE IT FOR
FINAL FOUR.
THIS IS NOTHING MORE THAN A SOUV
YEAR.
IT'S USELESS IN THIS GAME.
TODAY WAS THE LAST DAY I COULD
USE IT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE ONLY THING I HAVE GOING FOR
ME RIGHT NOW IS MY BLUFF BUT IF
I DON'T PULL THIS OFF AND I
DON'T WIN AN INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
NECKLACE, I MIGHT BE IN SERIOUS
TROUBLE SO CLOSE TO THE END
WHERE IT'S GOING TO HURT THE
MOST.
♪
>> TRISH HAD AN EVIL SIDE.
SHE WAS PRETTY HARSH YESTERDAY.
SHE HAS A HUGE CAPACITY TO HATE.
SHE HATES LINDSEY.
SHE HATES ME.
SHE HATES MORGAN.
WHY DOES SOMEONE HATE SOMETHING
SO MUCH?
TONY IS AN IDIOT.
PARANOID, AND EMOTIONAL.
AND LAST NIGHT, HE MADE A
PARANOID DECISION.
HE DIDN'T THINK ABOUT IT.
HE DIDN'T THINK THAT PEOPLE WERE
CAPABLE OF DISLIKING TRISH.
WHEN IN REALITY, I'M PRETTY SURE
ALMOST EVERYONE DISLIKES TRISH.
WHY SHOULD I LET HER WALK ALL
OVER ME?
>> SHE DIDN'T.
SHE'S OUT.
YOU WON.
YOU GET THE LAST LAUGH.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
>> I GET THAT.
I THINK THEY MADE A MISTAKE
YESTERDAY IN VOTING OUT TRISH,
BUT IT WASN'T ME, SO I DON'T
CARE.
AND TONY, I MEAN HE'S GOT ALL
THESE IDOLS.
>> I'M SAFE.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE SAFE.
>> I CAN DO WHATEVER I WANT.
THAT'S WHY I CAN GO AND BE COCKY
AND CONFIDENT IN MY GAME.
>> BUT HE HASN'T HAD TO DO MUCH.
HE WAS ON A WINNING TEAM ALL THE
WAY UP TO THE MERGE.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
MAYBE IT'S FINAL FOUR TREATMENT.
>> I HOPE IT'S LIKE A PICNIC.
A COUPLE OF BASKETS OF BREAD AND
CHEESE.
>> I'LL TAKE IT.
>> WHO'S THAT?
FOOD?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> THAT'S YOUR HUSBAND.
>> OH, MY GOD!
MY HUSBAND'S HERE.
>> WHAT?
WE WERE LAYING AROUND, AND IT
WAS, LIKE, THE "LOVE BOAT"
SHOWED UP, AND THERE WAS MY
HUSBAND.
THIS IS A HUGE PART OF ANYONE
OUT HERE'S LIFE.
SO, YEAH, I MIGHT CRY.
DAMN IT.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE-- WHERE
ARE MY DEVIL HORNS.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT I'VE BEEN
THROUGH.
>> I CAN IMAGINE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I'M NOT AN EMOTIONAL GUY, BUT
IT WAS POWERFUL.
>> EVERYONE GIVES YOU A HUG AND
A KISS.
>> RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME IS MY
SISTER, WHO LOVES ME
UNCONDITIONALLY, AND IT WAS THE
BEST SURPRISE OF THE GAME.
GAME.
>> MAN.
WHY COULDN'T SHE MAKE IT,
BECAUSE OF THE BABY?
I'M LOOKING AROUND, LOOKING
AROUND.
I WAS LOOKING FOR MY WIFE, AND I
DIDN'T SEE MY WIFE.
>> MAN, YOU LOOK LIKE A
DIFFERENT MAN.
>> I SEEN MY BEST FRIEND ARNOLD,
AND IT SUCKED BECAUSE I WAS
ANTICIPATING MY WIFE,UN.
I WAS LOOKING FORWARD TO SEEING
MY WIFE.
BUT I JUST DON'T THINK SHE COULD
LEAVE A FOUR-MONTH-OLD BABY TO
COME OUT HERE.
IT WAS HARD ENOUGH FOR ME TO DO
IT, BUT I KNOW IT WAS HER MOM'S
HANDS.
DID YOU SEE BABY BEFORE YOU GOT
HERE?
>> YES, YES.
>> HOW WAS SHE?
>> BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL.
GROWN, AWESOME.
WHEN YOU SEE HERK I MEAN, IT'S
GOING TO BE SUCH A CHANGE.
>> ARNOLD TOLD ME EVERYTHING
ABOUT MY LITTLE BABY.
HE TOLD ME-- HE TOLD ME THAT MY
BABY IS ALMOST TWICE THE SIZE.
I WAS SO HAPPY TO HEAR THAT.
YOU KNOW, MY DAUGHTER IS IN HER
MOM'S HANDS.
I'M AT PEACE.
>> HEY, WOO.
THIS IS MY FRIEND ARNOLD.
>> ARNOLD.
>> MARISSA COULDN'T MAKE TMAN.
>> YOUR WIFE'S DOING WELL, THE
BABY'S DOING AWESOME.
AFTER 37 DAYS OUT HERE, SEE
BLOOD, SEE FAMILY.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE FULFILLING.
MY LITTLE COUSIN MIKEY LOOKED
LIKE AN ANGEL.
I SAW HIS FACE-- AND YOU JUST
GET PSYCHED.
>> CONGRATS, EVERYBODY.
>> FINAL FOUR.
>> CONGRATS, GUYS.
>> CHEERS.
>> I THINK IT'S TIME FOR US TO
EAT, MAN.
>> YEAH.
>> I SEE SOME BREAD.
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY, SPENCE.
>> A BASKET OF MANGO JUICE AND
GRAPE JUICE.
OH!
IT WAS SO GOOD AND THEN WE HAVE
A FAT THING OF CRUNCHY PEANUT
BUTTER I HAVE BEEN DREAMING OF
FOR THE PAST 37 DAYS.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE SITTING THERE.
AND I'M LIKE HEY, YOU WANT TO
CHECK OUT TREE MAIL?
>> TREE MAIL.
>> OH, HOLD ON.
>> IT SAYS, NOT A GOOD TIME TO
BE AFRAID OF HEIGHTS.
GO AHEAD AND JUMP RIGHT ON IN.
YOU CAN BE THE NEXT TO JOIN THE
JURY UNLESS, OF COURSE, YOU WI
WIN."
IMMUNITY TODAY?
>> THAT'S WHAT IT SOUNDS LIKE.
>> WHAT!
>> I DON'T REALLY CARE.
>> I'M GOING TO WIN THIS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
I'M PICTURING IT NOW, SOLE
SURVIVOR, YOUNG WOO HUANG.
WINNER OF A MILLION DOLLARS.
AND I CAN PICTURE POSING WITH
CHRISTINA HAMILTON, MY LOVELY
GIRLFRIEND, AFTER GETTING
PERMISSION FROM HER MOM AND DAD,
OF COURSE.
STARTING MY FAMILY.
STARTING A LIFE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, ONE STEP AT A
TIME.
>>> YUP.
>> BUT IT'S GONE FAST.
DID IT GO FAST AT HOME?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> BUT I'M HERE.
>> YOU ARE HERE.
>> FINAL FOUR.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M NOT A GOAT.
I'M JUST HATED.
PEOPLE WILL COME DOWN ON ME,
ESPECIALLY THE WOMEN.
BUT I'M JUST GOING TO ARGUE TO
THE WOMEN THAT I CAME OUT HERE
AND I PLAYED LIKE A MAN, AND YOU
CAN'T FAULT ME FOR THAT.
IF I WERE A MAN AND I MADE ALL
THE MOVES I MADE, I WOULD BE-- I
WOULD BE STRATEGIC.
BUT BECAUSE I'M A WOMAN, I'M A
BITCH.
I DO RESPECT MY HUSBAND AND I
LOVE HIM.
AND I AM THE LAST WOMAN, YOU
KNOW.
I GUESS FOR HIM TO SEE THAT
PROBABLY SHOWS HIM A DIFFERENT
SIDE OF ME.
I'M JUST GOING TO BE LIKE,
"THINK ABOUT IT, GIRLS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU WANT ME TO COME OUT AND BE
YOUR MOMMA OR DO YOU WANT ME TO
COME OUT AND WIN?
WHAT'S THE BETTER ROLE MODEL."
HOPEFULLY PEOPLE WILL GIVE ME
CREDIT FOR THAT.
MY HUSBAND KNOWS I'M TENACIOUS.
HE'S SEEN ME BATTLE IN COURT AND
KICK SOME ASS, AND OFTEN CHAOS
IS A PART OF THAT, KEEPING THE
OTHER SIDE ON THEIR TOES.
>> I KNOW I'M GOING TO GIVE
EVERYTHING I HAVE, AND I CAN BE
AT PEACE WITH WHAT HAPPENS
BECAUSE I KNOW I'LL LEAVE HAVING
TRIED EVERYTHING I CAN TRY.
I HAVE TO GO INTO THIS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE OUT FOR BLOOD, READY
TO WIN IT'S ALL COSTS BECAUSE
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS MY SHOT AT THE MILLION
DOLLARS RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
IT'S DO OR DIE.
AND I DON'T PLAN ON DYING.
>> Jeff: AND YOU THOUGHT THERE
WASN'T GOING TO BE A LOVED ONE
VISIT.
ONE OF THE QUESTIONS I GET A LOT
IS WHILE THE FINALE IS GOING ON,
THIS FINAL TWO-HOUR EPISODE,
WHERE ARE THE CONTESTANTS?
TODAY, THEY'RE DOWN IN THE
BASEMENT HERE AT CBS IN THE
GREEN ROOM.
WE MADE A LITTLE "SURVIVOR"
LOUNGE.
COME ON IN.
IT'S ONLY THE PLAYERS.
THERE'S NO FAMILY MEMBERS IN
HERE.
WE'VE GOT-- YEAH, WOO TRYING TO
GET A LITTLE CAMERA TIME LIKE HE
HASN'T BEEN ON THE SHOW FOR THE
LAST THREE MONTHS.
JEREMIAH, J-TIA, SPENCER,
GARRETT.
HERE'S THE VIBE IN HERE TONIGHT.
BECAUSE SOMETIMES THE VIBE IS
UNCOMFORTABLE BECAUSE OF WHAT'S
GONE ON IN THE SHOW, BUT THIS
SEASON, I HAVE TO SAY, NOT ONLY
HAVE THEY PLAYED A REALLY GREAT
GAME, EVERYBODY IN HERE REALLY
DOES SEEM TO GET ALONG, AND I
THINK WE JUST HAD THE RIGHT
BALANCE.
THIS IS ONE OF THE GREAT GROUPS
OF ALL TIME IN "SURVIVOR.
OF OKAY, WE HAVE IT.
OUR FINAL FOUR.
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IS NEXT, AND
I'M TELLING YOU, IT IS ONE OF
THE BEST CHALLENGES YOU WILL SEE
ON THIS SHOW.
EPIC!
BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WELCOME, LOVED ONES.
SO, KASS, WHAT IS THAT LIKE TO
SEE YOUR HUSBAND ROLL UP IN A
BOAT?
>> GREAT SURPRISE.
ESPECIALLY FOR ME WHO AS WE ALL
KNOW, HAS BEEN A LITTLE HATED
OUT HERE.
>> Jeff: TONY, SO WHAT IS IT
WHEN YOU HAVE YOUR BUD WEYOU?
IS THERE A SENSE OF SAFETY THAT
FOR A MOMENT THERE'S SOMEONE
HERE I KNOW I CAN TRUST?
>> OH, ABSOLUTELY, JEFF.
I MEAN, EVERYBODY COULD AGREE TO
THAT.
ALLIANCES IN THE GAME, AND
ALLIANCEFROM CHILDHOOD FRIEND
FRIENDSHIP IN REAL LIFE IS
TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
ALLIANCES HERE, YOU COULD BREAK
THEM.
YOU COULD MAKE ALL THE PROMISES
YOU WANT TO ANYBODY YOU DON'T
KNOW.
BUT PEOPLE YOU GROW UP WITH,
PEOPLE YOU LOVE AND CARE ABOUT,
THOSE PROMISES ARE FOREVER,
JEFF.
IT'S NOT LIKE THE GAME AT ALL.
>> Jeff: CAN YOU GIVE US SOME
INSIGHT INTO SPENCER, JUST ONE
SENTENCE THAT WILL HELP ME
UNDERSTAND THIS YOUNG MAN?
>> THIS MAN IS NEUROTIC.
EVERYTHING HE DOES, HE DOES IT
LIKE FULL.
EVERYTHING-- HE'LL START A
HOBBY, SAY, YEAH, THIS IS KIND
OF COOL.
EXI TALK TO HIM A COUPLE OF
WEEKS LATER, "THIS IS MY WHOLE
LIFE!
."
>> Jeff: WOO, 37 DAYS IN, WHAT
IS IT LIKE TO HAVE A FAMILY
MEMBER?
WHAT DOES IT GIVE YOU TO HELP
YOU GET TO THE END?
>> IT REJUVENATES YOU, JEFF.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A SECOND
WIND, EXTRA MOTIVATION TO GO UP
ON THE TODAY AND KICK SOME BUTT.
>> Jeff: YOUR LOVED ONES HAVE
BEEN INVITED TO WATCH YOU
PARTICIPATE IN A VERY IMPORTANT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
SHALL WE GET TO IT?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS, FIRST,
SPENCER.
HAVE TO TAKE IT BACK.
>> HE'LL GET IT IN A SECOND.
>> Jeff: WOW, HIS SISTER JUST
AS CONFIDENT AS HE IS.
SEE IF YOU'RE RIGHT.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'LL BE
PERCHED ON TOP OF A POLE IN THE
OCEAN.
ON MY GO YOU'LL USE A BUCKET TO
RETRIEVE WATER.
YOU THEN POUR THAT WATER DOWN A
CHUTE, RAISING A KEY.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE KEY, SWIM BACK
TO SHORE, UNLOCK A BUNDLE OF
PUZZLE PIECES AND USE THEM TO
SOLVE A BLOCK PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH THEIR
PUZZLE WINS IMMUNITY.
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
THREE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY, SADLY, AFTER 37
DAYS, WILL BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> JEFF, THIS IS NO JOKE.
>> Jeff: IMAGINE THIS IS A
FOOT OFF THE GROUND.
>> THAT AIN'T WORKING.
>> COME OTONE!
>> KASS, DO YOU FEEL IT SHAKING?
>> YES, I'M TOTALLY FREAKED OUT,
TONY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO FOR IMMUNITY AND A
SPOT IN THE FINAL THREE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THE MORE WATER YOU GET IN THAT
BUCKET, THE MORE YOU HAVE TO
POUR DOWN THAT CHUTE.
>> COME OSPENCER!
>> Jeff: WIND IS GOING TO PLAY
A FACTOR TODAY.
SPENCER MOVING QUICKLY.
>> COME ON, TONE!
>> Jeff: TONY DOING A NICE
JOB.
A LOT OF MOVEMENT FOR TONY THAT
ROUND.
EVERYBODY OFF TO A QUICK START,
EXCEPT KASS.
NERVOUS THIS HIGH UP, THE WIND
IS BLOWING.
NOTHING'S EASY WHEN YOU GET TO
DAY 37 ON "SURVIVOR."
>> PULL IT UP!
WORK IT UP!
THERE YOU GO, BABE.
>> Jeff: KASS REALLY WOBBLING,
REALLY TAKING HER TIME.
>> THERE YOU GO, GET IT!
>> Jeff: THAT WAS A WASTE OF
TIME.
NONE OF THAT WATER GOT IN.
TONY WITH ANOTHER NICE POUR.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: SPENCER WITH A NICE
JOB.
>> THAT WAS A GOOD ONE!
>> LET'S GO, WOO!
>> Jeff: WOO WITH A NICE POUR.
HE'S IN THIS NOW.
IT IS SPENCER AND TONY RIGHT NOW
NECK AND NECK.
TONY HAS A GREAT SYSTEM GOING.
>> LET'S GO, TONE!
>> Jeff: KASS ONCE AGAIN,
NOTHING.
IT IS TONY IN THE LEAD, THEN
SPENCER, THEN WOO.
WOO WITH A NICE POUR.
>> COME ON, WOO!
>> Jeff: ONCE THAT KEY IS
CLOSE ENOUGH, YOU CAN REACH IT,
GRAB IT.
SPENCER WITH ANOTHER NICE POUR.
CAN HE REACH THE KEY?
NO, HE'S GOT TO GO AGAIN.
>> GO, TONE!
>> Jeff: THIS COULD DO IT FOR
TONY.
TONY CLOSE ENOUGH.
HE HAS THE KEY.
JUMP IN.
YOU'RE DONE HERE.
>> I CAN'T JUMP, IN JEFF.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SWIM.
>> Jeff: TONY GOING TO LOSE
SOME TIME.
HE'S GOT TO CLIMB DOWN.
ONCE AGAIN, TONY WITH AN EARLY
LEAD IN AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
KASS FALLING OUT OF IT.
>> COME ON, TONE!
>> Jeff: SPENCE WER A NICE
POUR.
WILL IT BE ENOUGH TO GET HIS
KEY?
SPENCER INCHES AWAY.
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: SPENCER HAS HIS TEAM.
>> JUMP!
>> Jeff: WOO WITH A NICE POUR.
WOO VERY CLOSE BUT CAN'T REACH
IT.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: KASS NOW STARTING TO
GET IN ON IT.
>> TONY, YOU'RE ON BLUE.
>> Jeff: TONY NOW BACK AT THE
BEACH.
SPENCER NOW PACK AT THE BEACH.
IT IS THE SAME WE HAD AT THE
LAST CHALLENGE.
TONY HAD AN EARLY LEAD BUT
SPENCER CAUGHT HIM AND PASSED
HIM.
>> COME ON, WOO!
>> Jeff: WOO WITH A NICE POUR.
HE'S GOT ENOUGH.
HE CAN REACH HIS KEY.
HE'S GOT IT!
WOO HAS THE KEY!
WOO SWIMMING IN NOW.
KASS THE LAST ONE LEFT OUT HERE.
KASS HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE
GETTING THE WAITER IN THE CHUTE.
THREE PEOPLE IN IT.
IT IS TONY WORKING ON HIS
PUZZLE.
SPENCER WORKING ON HIS PUZZLE.
WOO NOW BACK TO SHORE.
>> LET'S GO, WOO.
>> Jeff: IT IS A COMPLICATED
PUZZLE.
SOMETIMES THEY LOOK RIGHT BUT
THEY'RE IN THE WRONG SPOT.
SPENCER STARTING TO MAKE A
LITTLE PROGRESS ON HIS PUZZ PEM
TONY STILL TRYING TO FIGURE IT
OUT.
WOO JUST GETTING THE PIECES
UNTIED.
KASS STILL STRUGGLING OUT ON THE
PERCH.
>> THERE YOU GO!
THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: AN ABSOLUTE DISASTER.
KASS' ROPE STUCK NOW ON THE
CHALLENGE.
CAN'T USE YOUR ROPE TO GET THE
KEY.
GOING TO HAVE TO CLIMB DOWN AND
UNHOOK IT.
>> CLIMB DOWN AND GET IT OFF OF
THERE.
YOU HAVE, LIKE, TWO BUCKETS,
YOU'RE ON THE BEACH.
>> Jeff: SLOW GOING EARLY ON
FOR TONEY AND WOO.
>> COME ON, SPENCER!
>> Jeff: SPENCE WER ANOTHER
PIECE.
IT LOOKS GOOD FROM THIS SIDE.
SPENCER WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: KASS BACK IN IT.
>> THERE YOU GO, BABE.
>> Jeff: GOT TO GET THAT
BUCKET UP AND GET SOME MORE
WATER IN THAT CHUTE.
THREE PEOPLE HAVE MADE IT
THROUGH THIS SECTION AND WORKING
ON THE PUZZLE.
SPENCER MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS.
IF HE'S RIGHT.
>>, OF COURSE, HE'S RIGHT.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: KASS VERY CLOSE.
CAN SHE REACH IT?
KASS HAS HER KEY.
GET IN THE WATER!
>> JUMP, BABY!
>> Jeff: SWIM IT BACK, LET'S
GO!
>> COME ON, YOU CAN CATCH THEM!
>> Jeff: IT IS A COMPLICATED
PUZZLE.
YOU CAN EXPECT NOTHING LESS 37
DAYS INTO THIS GAME.
THERE IS A LOT OF TRIAL AND
ERROR.
TONY HASN'T HAD A LOT OF SUCCESS
WITH PUZZLES.
KASS BACK.
SHE CAN UNLOCK HER PUZZLE
PIECES.
>> IT'S YOUR STRONG SUIT, HONEY.
>> Jeff: KASS IS GOOD AT
PUZZLES, BUT SHE'S LOST A TON OF
TIME TO SPENCER, WOO, AND TONY.
TONY STILL LOOKING FOR HIS FIRST
IMMUNITY WIN.
SPENCER STILL IN THE SAME SPOT.
>> LOOK AT THE OTHER SIDE,
SPENCE!
>> Jeff: KASS SLOW AND STEADY
LIKE SHE ALWAYS DOES IN PUZZLES.
KASS NEVER PANICS.
TONY AND WOO TEND TO THROW
PIECES AROUND, MAKE QUICKER
MOVES.
SPENCE WER ANOTHER PIECE.
HE'S GETTING BACK ON TRACK.
KASS WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> YOU'RE GOOD.
THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: KASS WAS COMPLETELY
OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE BUT SHE'S
STILL FIGHTING.
TONY SWAPS ONE PIECE FOR
ANOTHER.
WOO CHANGING OUT PIECES.
SPENCE WER ANOTHER PIECE.
KASS MAKING SOME PROGRESS NOW,
STARTING TO CLOSE THE GAP.
KASS IS DEFINITELY BACK IN THIS
CHALLENGE AFTER A HORRIBLE
BEGINNING.
>> YOU GOT IT!
YOU ARE RIGHT ON THERE, HONEY.
THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: KASS NOW HAS THE
MOMENT PUP IT'S KASS AND
SPENCER.
SPENCER WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
IT IS NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
SPENCER DOWN TO A FEW PIECES
LEFT.
KASS DOWN TO A FEW PIECES LEFT.
>> OH, GOD!
>> Jeff: SPENCER AND KASS
BATTLING IT OUT FOR A GUARANTEED
SPOT IN THE FINAL THREE.
>> Jeff: SPENCER SO CLOSE.
CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: KASS TWO PIECES AWAY
FROM ONE OF THE BIGGEST
COMEBACKS THIS SEASON.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: KASS WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
>> OH!
YEAH!
>> Jeff: ACCOUNTABLE COMEBACK!
>> OH, BABY!
WOW.
MY GOSH!
AWESOME!
WHAT A DAY!
WHAT A DAY TO WIN IT!
>> I NEEDED YOU, BABE.
THAT'S ALL I NEEDED.
>> MY GOD, MAN.
>> Jeff: KASS COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
I HAVE RUN OUT OF SUPERLATIVES
TO DESCRIBE THE AMOUNT OF
COMEBACKS THIS SEASON.
COOPERATE HAVE COME AT A BETTER
TIME.
KASS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT AT TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHICH MEANS SHE
MAKES IT TO THE FINAL THREE.
AND AFTER 37 VERY TOUGH DAYS,
TONY, WOO, SPENCER, ONE OF YOU
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
TIME TO SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOUR
LOVED ONES.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> I HAD TO WIN, AND IT MEANT SO
MUCH, AND SO LOSING IN ITSELF IS
DEVASTATING, BUT TO LOSE TO A
BRAIN-DEAD WEASEL LIKE KASS.
THAT'S THE MOST HUMILIATING WAY
I COULD HAVE LOST TODAY.
BUT I CARE TOO MUCH TO GO OUT OF
A GAME LIKE THIS WITHOUT DOING
EVERYTHING I CAN.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY MY ASS OFF.
THE BEST PART OF TODAY IS I
GET TO SEND SPENCER HOME.
AND IT LEVELS THE PLAYING FIELD.
IT GIVES ME A FAR BETTER SHOT AT
WINNING.
>> I'M GLAD YOU GOT A CHANCE TO
WIN.
>> THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE, KASS.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> MY PLAN WHEN I FLIPPED WAS TO
TRY TO GO TO THE END WITH TWO
BRAWNS.
TODAY I SEALED MY FATE.
I'M GOING WITH TWO BRAWNS, AND I
FEEL GOOD AGAINST EITHER WOO OR
TONY.
THE CHALLENGE BEAST IS OUT.
YOU CAN'T PUT IT WAY.
>> I JUST THE WANTED ONE TIME TO
WEAR THAT NECKLACE, AND I CAN'T
WEAR IT EVER.
SPENCE EKASS, AND WOO ARE STILL
UNDER THE IMPRESSION I HAVE AN
IDOL I CAN USE AT IDOL FOYER SO
I STILL FEEL SAFE.
ALL I WANTED WAS TO WEAR THE
IMMUNITY NECKLACE ONE TIME.
I WANTED TO WIN ONE CHALLENGE.
>> TONY, IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
NOW, BUT COULD WE HAVE A
CONVERSATION RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M CRYING NOT GETTING A
CHANCE TO WEAR THE NECKLACE, AND
SPENCER SAID THAT'S WHAT I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
>> I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
BECAUSE I HAVE A FEEG OF WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN THE GAME AND I WANT
TO YOU HEAR IT BECAUSE I THINK
IT MIGHT MAKE YOU THINK A
LITTLE.
IT IS A FINAL TWO.
>> WHY ARE YOU SAYING THAT, MAN?
>> BECAUSE EVERY TIME-- AND THIS
IS SOMETHING A FAN CAN TELLUE
EVERY TIME AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, AT THE FINAL FOUR
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, JEFF DOESN'T
SAY A SPOT IN THE FINAL THREE.
HE SAYS A SPOT IN THE FINAL
THREE AND A CHANCE TO PLEADS
YOUR CASE FOR A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> I HEARD THAT.
>> IT'S FINAL TWO.
>> WE WALKED TO TREE MAIL, AND
HE SAID IT'S GOING TO BE FINAL
TWO THIS SEASON.
HE'S A SUPER FAN SO I'M
LISTENING TO HIM AND HE MAKES
ALL THE SENSE IN THE WORLD.
>> IF I LEAVE, YOU GO TO THE
FINAL THREE, THERE ARE NO IDOLS,
NOTHING.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> IT'S IMMUNITY-- AND WHOEVER
WINS IMMUNITY--
>> TAKES THE PERSON WITH.
>> AND SHE'LL TAKE WOO.
>> AND WHO DO YOU THINK WOO
WOULD TAKE?
>> KASS.
>> NOT A GREAT POSITION FOR YOU.
IF I'M THERE I'M STILL THE
PERSON PEOPLE WANT OUT.
IF IT'S ME, YOU AND, KASS, KASS
VOTES ME OUT OVER YOU.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> I'M TRYING TO MAKE A PITCH TO
TONE TOW KEEP ME, BELIEVING IT'S
A FINAL, TWO AND BEING THAT
THAT'S THE BEST WAY FOR HIM TO
GET TO THE END.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS THAT IF YOU
GO WITH WOO AND KASS, IF EITHER
OF THEM WIN--
>> I'M OUT.
>> YOU'RE SCREWED.
>> IT MAKES SENSE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AT FINAL FOUR, A TIE IS A
FIRE-MAKING COMPETITION.
A TIE IS A LOT BETTER THAN GOING
HOME.
IF IT'S A FINAL THREE, I
WOULDN'T EVEN TRY TO PLEAD A
CASE BECAUSE IT WOULD BE SO
OBVIOUS THEY NEED TO GO.
BUT I REALLY THINK IT MAKES
SENSE TO TAKE ME.
ME.
TONY IS MY LAST HOPE.
>> I JUST NEED TO THINK, MAN.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK SPENCE IS
WORKING ON?
>> PROBABLY WORKING ON GETTING
ME OUT.
>> WE WOULD BE STUPID NOT TO GET
RID OF SPENCE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I'M NOT CHANGING MY MIND
ON THAT.
>> OKAY, COOL.
>> NO MATTER WHAT TONY'S ANTICS
OR SHENANIGANS ARE.
>> I SIT DOWN WITH KASS AND
SHE'S LIKE, WE'RE VOTING FOR
SPENCER.
AND I'M LIKE PHEW!
GOOD.
BUT SPENCER IS STILL MAKING
MOVES, BEING TIRED, BEING
HUNGRY, BEING THIRSTY, I DON'T
RECALL WHAT HAPPENS IF IT'S A
TIE IN THE FINAL FOUR, HOW DOES
THAT WORK?
I KNOW I WON'T BE ABE TO VOTE.
SPENCER WON'T BE ABE TO VOTE.
THEN IF IT GOES TO ANOTHER TIE,
THEN, MAN, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO DRAW ROCKS?
THE JURY?
WE FIGHT FOR IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT HAPPENS?
IS THE FIRST ONE TO BE ABLE TO
MAKE A FIRE?
ANYTHING COULD HAPPEN AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> I KNOW I'M VOTING SPENCER.
AND I KNOW WOO IS VOTING
SPENCER.
IF TONY AND SPENCER VOTE WOO, IT
COULD END UP A TIE, WHICH IS
BROKEN AT THIS STAGE BY A
FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE.
DOES TONY WANT TO FORCE THAT?
SPENCER WOULD PROBABLY LOVE TO
TRY THAT OR TRY ANYTHING.
AND EITHER WAY, IT'S NOT ME.
SO FIRE OFF, DO WHATEVER YOU
BOYS WANT TO DO, TO MED WELYOUR
GAME, BUT I'M SITTING PRETTY AND
I'M NOT HANDING MY NECKLACE TO
ANYONE.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
SARAH.
MORGAN.
L.J.
JEREMIAH.
JEFRA.
TASHA.
AND TRISH VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
TODAY'S CHALLENGE.
KASS, YOU HAD A COMEBACK THAT IF
I HADN'T SEEN IT WITH MY OWN
EYES I WOULDN'T HAVE BELIEVED
IT.
>> JEFF, THERE WAS A POINT WHEN
I WAS THINKING, YOU KNOW, THIS
CHALLENGE IS GOING TO BE OVER,
AND I'M STILL GOING TO BE STUCK
UP HERE ON THIS GIANT POLE IN
THE WATER BECAUSE I AM SCARED TO
DEATH TO JUMP FROM THIS HEIGHT.
BUT HEARING MY HUSBAND'S VOICE
AND HAVING HIM ENCOURAGE ME, I
MEAN, JUST HAVING SOMEONE THERE
CHEERING ME ON, I KNEW IT.
>> Jeff: TONY, YOU GUYS GOT A
SURPRISE VISIT THIS MORNING FROM
YOUR LOVED ONES.
WHAT DID THAT DO TO THE SPIRIT
INSIDE YOU?
>> IT WAS BITTERSWEET, JEFF.
WE SAW A BOAT PULL UP.
I'M LOOKING THROUGH THE CROWD
HOPING TO SEE A SHORT BLOND
GREEN-EYED LADY WHICH IS MY
WIFE, AND I SEE MY FRIEND.
BUT I WAS VERY PLEASED TO SEE
HIM AND IT GIVES YOU A BIG LIFT,
A HUGE LIFT.
>> Jeff: SPENCER, THE LOOK OF
DESPAIR ON YOUR FACE WHEN KASS
WON THE CHALLENGE TODAY.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME IN 37 DAYS
I'VE SEEN EMOTION IF YOU.
>> TODAY WAS AN EMOTIONAL DAY
FOR ME.
I MEAN, THE LOVED ONES.
TONY SAYS IT WAS BITTERSWEET.
FOR ME, THAT WASN'T THE CASE.
IT SOFTENED ME UP.
AND MY SISTER SAID IT BEST TODAY
AT THE CHALLENGE EYE AM
NEUROTIC.
AND THIS WILL BITE IF I LEAVE
THE GAME TWO DAYS SHORT OF MY
DREAM.
>> Jeff: SO WHAT CASE DO YOU
MAKE?
>> I THINK TONY IS IN A GREAT
SPOT TO WIN.
RIGHT NOW, IF WE'RE LOOKING AT A
FINAL TWO, AND TONY TAKES ME
OUT, THEN IF KASS WINS OR IF WOO
WINS THE NEXT IMMUNITY, SHOULD
VOTE TONY OUT RIGHT BEHIND ME.
HOWEVER, IF TONY KEEPS ME IN THE
GAIRNLG VOTES OUT WOO, BECAUSE
KASS HAS IMMUNITY, THEN IF KASS
WINS OR IF TONY WINS, TONY GETS
TO THAT FINAL TWO.
AND I WILL SAY, TONY, IN FRONT
OF THE JURY, IF WE ENDED UP IN A
SITUATION WHERE I HAD TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN TAKING YOU AND SOMEONE
ELSE TO THE END, I WOULD TAKE
YOU, AND I WOULD ASK THE JURY DO
NOT VOTE FOR ME.
I WILL TAKE MYSELF OUT OF THE
RUNNING, IF I DID NOT HONOR
THAT.
>> THE WAY IT IS NOW, I WOULD BE
NERVOUS TO GO TO THE END WITH
YOU.
>> I THINK YOU WOULD BEAT ME
HANDILY, TONY.
YOU PLAYED THE BETTER GAME.
>> Jeff: WOO, HOW ABOUT FOR
YOU?
YOU'RE EITHER A PERFECT PERSON
TO TAKE TO THE END BECAUSE THE
STORY WILL BE WHAT DID WOO DO?
OR YOU'RE THE WORST PERSON TO
TAKE TO THE END BECAUSE YOU
HAVEN'T OFFENDED ANYBODY.
>> I'VE BEEN A PLAYER.
I'VE JUST BEEN A LITTLE MORE
INCONSPICUOUS BECAUSE I'M NOT
VERY OUTSPOKEN, BUT I'VE BEEN AN
INSTRUMENTAL PART IN THOSE BIG
MOVES.
>> Jeff: KASS, YOU'RE REALLY
IN AN INTERESTING SITUATION.
YOU ARE A PART OF THIS THREESOME
WITH TONEY AND WOO, BUT YOU
STARTED THE GAME WITH SPENCER.
YOU HAVE IMMUNITY AROUND YOUR
NECK.
SO IT GIVES YOU SOME FREEDOM TO
SIT BACK AND SAY I HAVE ONE
BULLET IN THIS GUN.
I AM GOING TO TAKE AT SHOT AND
SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> I LOVE OPTIONS JEFF.
WE CAN'T GET RID OF TONY
TONIGHT.
WOO IS A POTENTIALLY LIKABLE
PLAIB PLAIR THAT HASN'T BURNED
ANY BRIDGES AND HASN'T LIED TO
ANYONE.
SO IF IT'S A BITTER JURY, WOO
WILL WIN.
IF IT'S NOT A BITTER JURY, TONY
OR I HAVE A SHOT.
>> Jeff: IS THERE A PART OF
YOU CONCERNED, TONY, IF THERE IS
ANOTHER TRIBAL, YOU MOEB THE
TARGET.
>> WELL--
>> YES.
>> KASS, DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
BEAT ME OVER WOO?
>> I HAVE A BETTER CHANCE
AGAINST WOO, I THINK.
NOT TONY.
>> WHOA!
>> OH, SNAP.
OH, SNAP.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, YEAH, THAT MAKES ME THE
TARGET OF ELIMINATION FOR THE
NEXT ROUND.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHICH IS EXACTLY WHAT HE'S
SAYING.
>> IF WOO HAD HIS HEAD ON
STRAIGHT, HE WOULD TAKE KASS
OVER YOU.
KASS IS EASIER TO BEAT THAN YOU
ARE, AND KASS WOULD TAKE WOO
OVER YOU, MEANING YOU WOULD HAVE
TO WIN IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KASS, YOU'RE UP.
>> I MADE THE ONLY ARGUMENT I
COULD MAKE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> JEFF.
I JUST WANT TO EXPLAIN THE
SPECIAL IDOL.
IT SAYS THIS IDOL CAN BE PLAYED
AFTER THE VOTE ARE READ.
THAT'S THE SPECIAL POWERS THAT
THIS IDOL HAS.
HOWEVER IT CAN ONLY BE PLAYED
WITH FIVE REMAINING PLAYERS
LEFT.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME I CAN PLAY
IT.
TODAY THERE ARE ONLY FOUR, SO
THIS IDOL IS ABSOLUTELY USELESS
TONIGHT.
SO THE WAY I USED IT TONIGHT IS
BY WEARING IT AROUND MY NECK.
IF MY NAME APPEARS THREE TIMES,
I'M GOING HOME TONIGHT.
I HOPE THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE.
SPENCER.
WOO.
ONE VOTE SPENCER, ONE VOTE WOO.
SPENCER.
THAT'S TWO VOTES SPENCER, ONE
VOTE WOO.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE EIGHTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
SPENCER.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
SPENCER, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> ADIOS.
>> Jeff: WELL, CONGRATULATIONS
ON MAKING IT TO THE FINAL THREE.
TOMORROW, YOU'LL COMPETE IN YOUR
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
TRY TO GET SOME SLEEP.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> I GAVE THE ONLY ARGUMENT I
COULD AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT WAS TOUGH.
I'M HEATED.
"SURVIVOR" ISN'T A GAME FOR ME.
"SURVIVOR "IS A APPROXIMATION
FOR ME.
SO 37 DAYS OF "SURVIVOR" BEING
MY LIFE AND THAT BEING OVER IS A
TOUGH PILL TO SWALLOW.
I THINK I LEARNED A LOT FROM THE
GAME, AND SOMETHING CAN COME OF
THIS MISERY THAT WAS "SURVIVOR."
YOU'RE FEELING AT HOME, BUT WE
HAVE AN EXCITED AUDIENCE.
BUT I WAS GOING TO SAY WE HAVE A
LOT OF DISAPPOINTED PEOPLE IN
THE HOUSE BECAUSE SPENCER WAS
ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR PLAISHZ
THIS SEASON.
YOU SAW HIM WALKING OUT OF
TRIBAL.
AND I GET THIS QUESTION A LOT--
THEY'RE WALKING.
WHERE ARE THEY GO?
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S LITERALLY WHAT
HAPPENS SECONDS AFTER THEY ARE
VOTED OUT.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I'M A LITTLE FIRED PUP.
I FEEL LIKE I COULD HAVE DONE
BETTER AND SHOULD HAVE DONE
BETTER.
>> 136.
>> WHAT!
>> BLOOD PRESSURE, HEART RATE.
>> THE LAST TIME I WEIGHED 136,
I PROBABLY HADN'T KISSED A GIRL
YET.
>> Jeff: WE ARE WITH JOANNIE,
SPENCER'S MOM.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
I JUST HAVE ONE QUESTION.
SPENCER AND I HAVE HAD A FUN,
VOLATILE RELATIONSHIP, BUT DID
YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHEN HE
FINALLY GOT ON THAT HE WOULD
LAST THIS LONG?
>> WHEN HE LEFT TO GO TO THE
AIRPORT, KAREN AND I LOOKED AT
EACH OTHER AND SAID HE'S GOING
TO BE ONE OF THE FIRST TO GO.
>> Jeff: WHICH IS WHAT I
THOUGHT.
OOB.
BUT YOU HATE TO SEE HIM GO, BUT
THAT'S WHY WINNING IS SO SWEET
BECAUSE THIS GAME IS SOATIVELY.
YOU GUYS ARE NOT FROM CA
>> I'M FROM TULSA, OKLAHOMA AND
WE DROVE OVER 24 HOURS TO GET
HERE.
>> Jeff: THAT'S A "SURVIVOR"
FAN.
ADAM, ONE OF OUR SOLDIERS,
FOUGHT IN AFGHANISTAN.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
SEVERELY INJURED.
YOU HAD 120 SURGERIES?
>> ROUGHLY, JEFF, YES.
>> Jeff: AND IS THIS TRUE, OR
ARE YOU JUST SAYING THAT?
PART OF YOUR RECOVERY WAS
BONDING WITH YOUR FAMILY OVER
"SURVIVOR?"
>> THAT'S CORRECT, YES.
>> Jeff: WE ARE REALLY GLAD
YOU'RE HERE.
REALLY GLAD YOU'RE IN THE
FAMILY.
WE GOT A THANS CHANS TO TALK
EARLIER.
VERY COOL DUDE.
WE'RE DOWN TO THREE, WOO, KASS,
TONY.
IT'S A FINALE, THAT'S WHAT IT
IS.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> CONGRATS, EVERYBODY.
>> CONGRATS.
>> FINALLY.
>> TRIBAL TONIGHT, THINGS WENT
AS PLANNED, SURPRISE WILL, FOR
ONCE.
AND SPENCE WENT HOME.
>> WHAT DO YOU GUYS, THINK, MAN?
ANOTHER IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
TOMORROW.
>> I'M OVER IT.
>> I MEAN, THERE'S ALWAYS AN
EXCITEMENT THAT YOU MAKE THE
TIME THREE.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO MEAN SOMETHING
SPECIAL.
>> MAN, WE COULD HAVE BEEN
CELEBRATING RIGHT NOW, FINAL
THREE.
>> I KNOW, WE'RE LIKE THE MOST
DEPRESSING TOP THREE.
INSTEAD WE COME BACK AND REALIZE
ONE OF THE THREE OF US IS GOING
HOME, AND I THINK THE BOYS ARE
MORE DEPRESSED ABOUT IT THAN ME
BECAUSE THEY MAY HAVE TO GO AT
EACH OTHER'S THROAT.
>> YOU CAN BELIEVE THAT, MAN?
>> IT IS WHAT IT IS, GUYS.
>> ONE OF US IS GOING TO BE
GOING HOME.
WHEN IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN ALL
THREE OF US GOING TO THE FINAL,
JURY.
>> I BELIEVE I WILL BE TAKEN TO
THE FINAL TWO IF I DON'T WIN
IMMUNITY, BECAUSE BOTH WOO AND
TONY BELIEVE THEY CAN BEAT ME.
THIS GAME CHANGES EVERY DAY.
>> EVERY DAY.
>> HUH?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT NEEDS TO
HAPPEN.
>> TONY CAN'T WIN.
>> EXACTLY.
I GOTTA KICK ASS.
>> I'M TAKING YOU, OR YOU'RE
TAKING ME, RIGHT?
>> YES, ABSOLUTELY.
YOU GOTTA WIN AND I GOTTA WIN.
KASS PRETTY MUCH SAID SHE HAS A
BETTER CHANCE OF BEATING ME AT
THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL, SO IF
SHE WINTOMORROW'S FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, CHANCES OF HER TAKING
ME WITH HER SEEMS GOOD.
IF I WIN, I'LL TAKE KASS TO THE
END AS WELL.
WE GOT NO SHOT AGAINST TONY.
>> I KNOW.
DON'T LET HIM TALK YOU INTO IT,
EITHER.
>> I MEAN, KASS, I'D BE THE
STUPIDEST SURVIVOR PLAYER TAKING
TONY TO THE END.
>> ME, TOO.
>> MOST RIDICULOUS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WELCOME TO YOUR FINAL CHALLENGE.
YOUR FACES SAY IT ALL.
PRETTY MASSIVE.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO IT?
>> SURE.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
KASS, TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
>> HOLY COW.
>> THIS IS UNREAL.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU ARE
GOING TO RACE THROUGH A MAZE OF
TURNSTILES.
SOME WILL TURN, SOME WON'T.
YOU'LL BE COLLECTING FOUR
MEDALLIONS ALONG THE WAY.
YOU'LL USE THE MEDALLIONS TO
OPEN A CHEST.
INSIDE THE CHEST ARE COGS THAT
WHEN ARRANGED CORRECTLY WORK
TOGETHER TO RAISE A FLAG.
FIRST PERSON TO RAISE THEIR FLAG
WINS IMMUNITY, IS GUARANTEED A
SPOT AT THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE YOU WILL GET A CHANCE TO
PLEAD YOUR CASE TO A JURY OF
YOUR PEERS ABOUT WHY YOU DESERVE
THE TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND
THE MILLION DOLLARS THAT GOES
WITH IT.
HUGE POWERS IN THIS CHALLENGE.
WIN, YOU CONTROL YOUR FATE.
LOSE, YOUR DESTINY IS IN
SOMEBODY ELSE'S HANDS.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A GUARANTEED
SPOT IN THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
SOME TURN, SOME DON'T.
IF THEY DON'T TURN, YOU'RE
BLOCKED.
YOU HAVE TO FIND ANOTHER PATH.
TONEY AND WOO QUICKLY GET TO THE
FIRST STATION.
KASS AT HER FIRST STATION.
ONCE YOU'VE GOT A MEDALLION
UNTIED, BRING IT BACK, GO OUT
FOR YOUR NEXT ONE.
TONY COMING BACK WITH HIS FIRST
MEDALLION, MAKING QUICK WORK OF
IT.
KASS HEADING BACK.
WOO HEADING BACK.
TONY BACK WITH HIS FIRST
MEDALLION.
WOO'S RIGHT . HIM WITH HIS
FIRST.
KASS IS BACK.
WOO JUST FOLLOWING TONY.
STEP FOR STEP.
TONY RUNS INTO A BLOCK.
KASS IS AT HER SECOND STATION.
KASS NOW IN THE LEAD.
WORKING ON HER SECOND MEDALLION.
WOO ANOTHER BLOCK.
TONY NOW BACK IN THE LEAD.
HE RUNS INTO A BIG BLOCK.
BOTH THOSE ARE GOING TO HURT.
KASS HAS HER SECOND MEDALLION.
SHE'S JUST GOT TO GET BACK OUT
OF THE MAZE WITH IT.
TONEY AND WOO HAVE BEEN CIRCLING
THE SAME STATION FOR A LONG TIME
BUT CAN'T GET THERE.
TONY FINALLY FIND IT, WOO RIGHT
ON HIS TAIL.
KASS IS THROUGH AND BACK WITH
HER SECOND MEDALLION, HEADING
OUT FOR HER THIRD.
THERE ARE FOUR TOTAL.
WOO NOW HAS HIS SECOND
MEDALLION.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
TONY NOW HEADING BACK.
KASS BACK OUT ON THE COURSE
LOOKING FOR HER THIRD, AS TONY
AND WOO ARE HEADING BACK WITH
THEIR SECOND.
NOW, TONY'S THROUGH.
TONY'S BACK WITH HIS SECOND
MEDALLION.
WOO FOUND A PATHWAY BACK WITH
HIS SECOND.
EVERYBODY HAS TWO MEDALLIONS
BACK.
KASS FOUND HER WAY QUICKLY TO
THE THIRD MEDALLION.
KASS BACK IN THE LEAD AGAIN.
WOO FIND HIS WAY TO THE THIRD
STATION.
TONY RIGHT BEHIND.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR THIRD
MEDALLION.
KASS HAS HER THIRD MEDALLION.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
>> HOW DOES DSHE GET THREE
ALREADY?
>> Jeff: KASS IS BACK WITH HER
THIRD MEDALLION.
ONE LEFT FOR KASS.
TONEY AND WOO STILL WORKING ON
THOSE KNOTS.
TONY LOSES HIS.
YOU CAN FEEL THE PANIC SETTING
IN.
WOO RACING BACK WITH HIS THIRD.
TONY RIGHT BEHIND HIM WITH HIS
THIRD.
EVERYBODY LOOKING FOR THEIR
FOURTH AND FINAL MEDALLION.
THIS IS IT.
KASS KNOWS WHERE SHE HAS TO GO.
SHE'S JUST GOT TO FIND IT.
THIS IS THE ONE THAT PROVED SO
DIFFICULT FOR TONEY AND WOO.
TONY AND WOO KNOW WHERE THEY
HAVE TO GET TO.
IT'S A LONG WAYS AWAY.
THEY HAVE SEPARATED FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN THIS MAZE.
WOO IS ON HIS OWN.
TONY IS ON HIS OWN.
KASS CAN SEE THE MEDALLION, BUT
SHE'S GOT TO GET THERE FIRST.
NO, ANOTHER DEAD END.
WOO GETTING CLOSER.
WOO THE FIRST TO HIS FOURTH
STATION.
WORKING ON THAT FOURTH
MEDALLION.
KASS STILL TRYING TO GET IN TO
THAT VERY DIFFICULT STATION.
TONY NOW TRYING TO FIND WOO.
HE SEPARATED FROM HIM.
FOR THE FIRST TIME THIS THIS
CHALLENGE, AND IT IS COSTING
HIM.
TONY RACING TO GET BACK THERE.
TONY AT THE STATION FOR HIS
FOURTH MEDALLION.
WOO HAS HIS FOURTH MEDALLION.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
WOO WITH THE LEAD NOW.
KASS STRUGGLING TO FIND THAT
FOURTH MEDALLION.
SHE CAN'T GET TO IT.
TONY HAS HIS FOURTH MEDALLION.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
WOO FIND HIS WAY OUT WITH THAT
FOURTH MEDALLION.
OPEN UP THE CHEST.
KASS HAS FINALLY FOUND THAT
FOURTH STATION.
WORKING ON HER FOURTH MEDALLION.
TONY HAS FOUND HIS WAY OUT.
TONY NOW CAN OPEN HIS CHEST.
KASS HAS HER FOURTH MEDALLION.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
WOO HAS ALL THE COGS UNTIED.
HE CAN START SOLVING THIS
PUZZLE.
TONY UNTYING HIS COGS.
VERY DIFFICULT PUTTING THESE
GEARS TOGETHER.
WHEN YOU HAVE IT RIGHT, YOU WILL
KNOW, AND IT WILL RAISE A FLAG.
YOU'LL BE SITTING AT FINAL
TRIBAL.
KASS HAS HAD GOOD LUCK COMING
FROM BEHIND IN CHALLENGES.
SHE WILL NEED IT TODAY.
WOO AND TONY ALREADY WORKING ON
THEIR PUZZLE.
KASS HAS FOUND HER WAY OUT.
KASS NOW BACK WITH HER FOURTH
MEDALLION.
EVERYBODY'S GOING TO BE WORKING
ON THIS PUZZLE.
KASS HAS GOT TO GET THAT CHEST
OPEN AND GET TO WORK.
TONEY AND WOO WITH A BIG LEAD.
WOO ALREADY HAS SEVERAL PIECES
TOGETHER.
IF THEY'RE RIGHT.
AS ALWAYS, THAT'S THE BIG
QUESTION.
IS IT RIGHT?
KASS IS IN DEAD LAST, A SPOT SHE
HAS FOUND HERSELF IN MANY TIMES
BEFORE.
SHE MANAGED TO PULL OUT ONE OF
THE BIGGEST COMEBACKS AT THE
LAST CHALLENGE.
CAN SHE DO IT AGAIN?
WOO HAS TASTED INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY ONE TIME.
HE WOULD LOVE TO HAVE IT AGAIN
RIGHT NOW.
TONY HAS NEVER WON INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
AND IT COULDN'T COME AT A BETTER
TIME THAN RIGHT NOW.
KASS CATCHING UP.
CLOSING THE GAP.
WOO VERY CLOSE.
DOWN TO HIS LAST TWO PIECES.
KASS IS NOW BACK IN THIS.
SHE'S ONLY GOT TWO PIECES LEFT.
WOO'S DOWN TO HIS LAST PIECE.
KASS IS DOWN TO HER LAST PIECE.
THIS IS GOING TO COME DOWN TO
THE WIRE.
WOO HAS IT.
WOO WINS IMMUNITY!
KASS ONE SECOND BEHIND.
WOO GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE
FINAL TWO.
KASS, YOU WERE LITERALLY A HALF
A SECOND.
>> I KNOW.
DAMN IT.
WOO, COME ON OVER.
COULDN'T HAVE COME AT A BETTER
TIME.
WITH THIS NECKLACE, YOU ARE
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
EQUALLY IMPORTANT, YOU GET TO
DECIDE TONIGHT WHO SITS NEXT TO
YOU AT THAT FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
BIG DECISION.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: CONGRATS.
>> IF YOU'RE IN THE OLYMPICS,
AND YOU RUN THE MARATHON, AND
YOU LOSE BY HALF A SECOND,
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
IT'S CRAZY.
AND I NEEDED IT.
I NEEDED TO BE ABLE TO MAKE THIS
DECISION.
I THINK WOO MIGHT BE ABLE TO
BEAT ME.
I DON'T KNOW.
I HOPE HE THINKS SO.
>> Jeff: THAT WAS PROBABLY THE
CLOSEST FINISH IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY.
IT TRULY WAS LESS THAN HALF A
SECOND, AND IT WOULD BE A
MILLION-DOLLAR WIN FOR WOO IF HE
CHOOSES THE RIGHT PERSON TO TAKE
TO THE END.
WHO DO YOU TAKE IF YOU'RE WOO?
>> PROBABLY KASS BECAUSE
NOBODY-- I THINK NOBODY REALLY
HAS RESPECT FOR HER.
>> Jeff: GOOD JOB.
YOU'D BE GREAT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN WATCHING?
>> PROBABLY SINCE I WAS EIGHT,
SO, LIKE, THREE YEARS.
>> Jeff: THREE YEARS.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO THAT
MEANS YOU'RE 11.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: JUST CHECKING MY
MATH.
DO YOU WATCH OLD EPISODES
ONLINE.
>> ON iTUNES, IF I'M BORED OR
SICK.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU GUYS
BASICALLY CAUGHT UP WITH THE
HISTORY OF "SURVIVOR?"
>> YES.
>> Jeff: EVEN THOUGH THE SHOW
WAS ON LONG BEFORE MOST OF YOU
GUYS WERE BORN ONE YEAR BEFORE
YOU WERE BORN?
THIS IS WHY I LOVE "SURVIVOR."
THIS IS ONE OF THE BEST PART OF
THE JOB, TRULY, MEETING KIDS
LIKE THIS WHO LOVE ADVENTURE.
AND I KNOW THERE ARE A LOT OF
YOU AT HOME TONIGHT WHO ARE THE
SAME AGE.
YOU'RE DIEHARD FANS.
YOU CAN SMELL THE CAMPED FIRE ON
YOUR CLOTHES, TASTE THE RICE,
BUT YOU'RE NOT QUITE OLD ENOUGH
YET.
REMEMBER, MALCOLM, COCHRAN,
THOSE GUYS.
THEY WERE LITTLE KIDS.
WE LASTED LONG ENOUGH FOR THEM.
AND IF WE STAY ON LONG ENOUGH,
WHO KNOWS YOU MIGHT JUST GET THE
CHANCE, AND I HAVE TO SAY THIS,
I CANNOT WAIT TO SNUFF YOUR
TORCH.
AND THAT GOES FOR YOU GUYS, TOO.
ALL RIGHT, THE FINAL TRIBAL IS
NEXT.
39 DAYS COMES TO A HEAD.
GOOD JOB!
>> NICE JOB, WOO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HALF A SECOND, I WAS TURNING
WHILE YOU WERE TURNING.
>> GROWING UP IN TAIWAN DOUGH, I
WON JUNIOR OLYMPIC
CHAMPIONSHIPS.
I WON NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIPS.
I WON GRAND CHAMPIONSHIP.
THIS RIGHT HERE, MY FRIEND,
DEFINITELY TAKES THE CAKE.
I WON THE ULTIMATE PRIZE.
YES!
STOKED!
>> BUT NOW IT'S SCRAMBLE TIME.
>> BOY, YOU'RE GOING TO BE A
BUSY MAN TODAY, MY FRIEND.
VERY BUSY MAN.
>> I WAS PSYCHED TO BE WEARING
THIS, BUT THEN AGAIN, I GOT KIND
OF THIS UNEASY FEELING IN MY
STOMACH LIKE, MAN, THE FACT THAT
I NOW HAVE TO CHOOSE EITHER TONY
OR KASS TO COME WITH ME, IT'S SO
NUTS.
>> WOO, ARE WE READY?
LET'S GO FOR A WALK MY MAN.
I HAVE TO POLITIC RIGHT NOW.
>> HERE I AM DAY 38 AND NOW MY
DESTINY LIES IN WOO'S HAND.
MY BACK IS UP AGAINST THE WALL.
HE IS NOT GOING TO BE SO EASY TO
CONVINCE TO VOTE AGAINST KASS.
I'LL EXPLAIN WHY YOU HAVE EVERY
REASON TO BE NERVOUS ABOUT GOING
WITH KASS.
THERE'S NO TRICKERY HERE.
YOU'RE IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT, MY
MAN.
NOTHING CAN HAPPEN TO YOU FROM
THIS POINT ON.
YOU'RE GOOD.
SO I WANT TO BE AS SUBTLE, AS
SOFT AS I CAN, BUT AT THE SAME
TIME, AGGRESSIVE.
I'M JUST PLANTING THE SEEDS ONCE
AGAIN.
HOPING SOMETHING CATCHES.
YOU'RE A TAE KWON DO INSTRUCTOR
YOU HAVE INTEGRITY, AND LOYALTY.
YOU WERE LOYAL TO ME FROM DAY
ONE.
YOU CAN SAY YOU WERE LOYAL, AND
HONOR AND INTEGRITY.
IF YOU'RE IN CONTROL, IF YOU'RE
IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT, AND YOU
TAKE KASS, YOU HAVE ZERO CHANCE
OF WINNING.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT OR NO?
>> WHY IS THAT?
>> KASS HAS STORIES.
SHE DID STUFF, EVEN THOUGH THEY
WERE WRONG MOVES, BUT SHE
PLAYED.
SHE PLAYED THE GAME, AS OPPOSED
TO YOU DIDN'T.
TAKING SOMEONE LIKE KASS,
THINKING YOU'RE GOING TO RUN
AWAY WITH IT IS GOING TO BE YOUR
DEMISE.
YOU HAVE A BETTER SHOT TAKING ME
THAN YOU DO WITH KASS.
THAT'S HOW THE GAME GOES.
THAT'S HOW THE GAME GOES, WOO.
MY ARGUMENT TO WOO IS A PRETTY
VALID ARGUMENT.
WOO HAS BASED HIS GAME AROUND
LOYALTY, HONOR, INTEGRITY, AND
SO I'M TELL HIM, WOO, FINAL TWO,
FOR TO YOU OUST ME NOW.
YOU JUST THREW YOUR GAME PLAN
OUT THE WINDOW.
>> TONY, I RESPECT YOU IN A BIG
WAY.
AND I'M GOING TO CONSIDER
EVERYTHING YOU SAY.
>> I KNOW.
>> I CAN'T GIVE YOU MY WORD NOW.
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO.
YOU DON'T NEED TO, BRO.
>> I'LL DEFINITELY THINK ABOUT
IT.
>> IS HE BUYING IT?
I WOULDN'T BUY IT.
I'D TAKE MY CHANCES WITH KASS.
>> REMEMBER WHAT TONY'S BEEN
TELLING YOU THIS WHOLE TIME IS
TAKE KASS, TAKE KASS, BECAUSE WE
CAN BEAT HER.
RIGHT?
>> I HEAR THAT.
>> WHY WOULD HIS REASONING
CHANGE RIGHT NOW.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HE CARRIED ME ALL THIS WAY
BECAUSE HE KNEW I'M UNLIKABLE.
TO ME, YOU ARE LIKE FABIO RIGHT
NOW.
YOU HAVEN'T REALLY HURT ANYBODY.
NOBODY REALLY KNOWS YOU.
EVERYBODY HATES ME.
BUT IF GUWITH TONY, TONY'S GOING
TO SAY, "I PULLED HIM ALONG.
WE HURT THE SAME PEOPLE, BUT I
MADE THE MOVES.
WHY SHOULD HE GET THE MONEY WHEN
I DID ALL THE WORK."
THAT'S WHAT I WOULD SAY IF I WAS
TONY.
IF I'M ON THERE, I'M VOTING FOR
BECAUSE HE PLAYED THE BEST GAME.
WOO IS LIKE A CUTE SURFER DUDE,
AWESOME, COOL.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
HOW DO I SPELL THEIR NAME?
THIS IS SO INSANE RIGHT NOW.
BUT I HEAR YOU 100%.
>> YEAH.
IT'S HORRIFYING.
THE PERSON WHO HASN'T MADE A
DECISION THE WHOLE GAME IS IN
CHARGE OF MY FATE.
>> I'M GOING TO TELL YOU EXACTLY
WHAT I TOLD TONY.
I'M GOING TO TAKE A DAY TO THINK
ABOUT THE PROS AND CONS OF BOTH
ARGUMENTS, AND I'LL JUST MAKE MY
DECISIONA TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
>> I RESPECT THAT.
I WANT WOO TO DO WHAT'S BEST FOR
HIM, WHICH IS TO TAKE ME.
IF HE UNDERSTANDS HOW PEOPLE
THINK, TAKING ME IS HIS BETTER
OPTION.
REALLY.
>> I WOULD FEEL MORE COMFORTABLE
SITTING AT THE END WITH TONY.
THIS IS THE GUY I STARTED WITH.
THIS IS THE GUY I COMMITTED
MYSELF WITH.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY, LIKE,
TAKING TONY MEANS MY CHANCES OF
WINNING ARE NOT SO GREAT.
OH, BRO.
IF I TAKE SOMEONE LIKE KASS, YOU
KNOW, AND I BREAK MY LOYALTY
WITH TONY, IT COMPLETELY
CONTRADICTS WHO I AM.
AND I BECOME THE BIGGEST
HYPOCRITE.
SO IT'S TOUGH.
I WANT TO BE A SOLE SURVIVOR.
AND TO HAVE A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
SARA, MORGAN.
L.J.
JEREMIAH.
JEFRA.
TASHA.
TRISH.
AND SPENCER, VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, WOORKS AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, TONY IN PARTICULAR HAD
A BIG DECISION-- STAY TRUE TO
YOU, SOMEBODY HE'S PLAYED THE
GAME WITH GOING BACK TO DAY ONE.
OR GET RID OF YOU AND TAKE HIS
CHANCES WITH SPENCER.
HE STAYED TRUE TO YOU.
AND TODAY YOU MADE HIM PAY FOR
IT.
HOW DID THAT FEEL IN THAT MOMENT
WHEN YOU KNEW I'D LOCKED IN A
SPOT IN THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL?
>> AMAZING, JEFF.
I KNEW THAT IF THERE'S ONE DAY I
NEEDED TO DO WELL AT A PUZZLE,
IT WAS TODAY.
AND TO BE ABLE TO WEAR THIS
TONIGHT, I'M-- I'M ABSOLUTELY
HONORED.
I'M GRATEFUL.
I'M NERVOUS.
>> Jeff: DO YOU THINK LAST
NIGHT'S VOTE WAS A TESTAMENT
FROM TONY TO YOU ABOUT LOYALTY
OR DO YOU THINK IT WAS STRICTLY
STRATEGY?
>> I THINK TONY'S VOTE LAST
NIGHT WAS STRATEGIC, BUT FOR THE
MOST PART, HIS LOYALTY AND
COMMITMENT TO ME.
>> Jeff: TONY, HINDSIGHT IS
ALWAYS 20/20.
DID YOU SPEND ANY TIME THINKING,
HOW MIGHT THIS HAVE GONE DOWN IF
I WOULD HAVE BETRAYED MY LOYALTY
TO WOO AND TOOK MY SHOT WITH
SPENCER?
>> I MIGHT HAVE A DIFFERENT
ANSWER AFTER TONIGHT, BUT FOR
NOW I'M GOING TO ANSWER NO.
THIS IS THE EXACT SCENARIO THAT
SPENCER PROPOSED TO ME.
HE SAID IF WOO WINS IMMUNITY,
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE, TONY.
TONIGHT IS GOING TO BE THE
NIGHT.
I WAS LOYAL TO WOO.
I KNOW WOO'S GAME PLAY WAS
LOYALTY, NOT TO EVERYBODY ELSE
BUT TO ME DAY ONE.
HERE WE ARE, DAY 38.
IT'S HIS TIME TO SHINE.
>> Jeff: KASS, IT WAS PROBABLY
LESS THAN ONE SECOND THAT
SEPARATED YOU AND WOO AT THE
FINISH.
>> I BELIEVE YOU SAID IT WAS A
HALF A SECOND.
UMM, I HAVE RELIVED THAT
CHALLENGE ALL AFTERNOON.
THERE ARE SO MANY THINGS I COULD
HAVE DONE TO MAKE UP A
MILLISECOND.
BUT I CAN'T GO BACK.
I MEAN, I'M HERE.
AND WOO WON, AND HE WON FAIR AND
SQUARE.
AND IT WAS EXCRUCIATING.
IT'S BEEN A ROUGH AFTERNOON.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S BEEN THE
ROUGHEST PART, THE REPLAYING OR
THE WONDERING NOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN?
MY FATE IS NOT IN MY HANDS?
>> THE LOSS OF CONTROL OF YOUR
OWN FATE.
YOU JUST FEEL SICK ALL
AFTERNOON.
YOU KNOW, WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN?
WHAT'S WOO GOING TO DO?
IS HE LOYAL TO TONY TO THE POINT
OF POTENTIALLY LOSING A MILLION
DOLLARS?
>> Jeff: SO WOO WERE YOU
APPROACHED BY BOTH KASS AND TONY
TODAY?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: EXPECTED, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: AND WHAT WERE THEIR
BASIC PITCHES?
>> YOU MIND IF I GO OFF SUBJECT?
>> Jeff: YEAH.
>> OKAY, I HOPE THESE TWO WILL
UNDERSTAND MY DECISION.
AND I JUST WANT TO GET TO THE
VOTE.
>> Jeff: YOU DON'T EVEN WANT
TO HEAR FROM KASS AND TONY.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S HOW THE VOTE WILL WORK.
NOBODY CAN VOTE FOR WOO, WHICH
MEANS KASS YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR
TONY, TONY CAN ONLY VOTE FOR
KASS.
YOUR VOTES CANCEL EACH OTHER OUT
SO YOU WON'T VOTE.
THE ONLY PUBLISH VOTING IS YOU,
WOO.
YOU'RE VOTING OUT THE 15th
PERSON OF THE GAME, THE NINTH
PERSON OF THE JURY, AND YOU'LL
BE DECIDING WHO YOU'RE GOING TO
SIT WITH TOMORROW AT FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
WOO, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO GET THE VOTE.
ONCE THE VOTE IS READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTE.
15th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE NINTH AND FINAL MEMBER OF
OUR JURY KASS.
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> THANK YOU, WOO, MAN.
>> Jeff: KASS, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WOO AND TONY, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN
GO IN THIS GAME.
TOMORROW NIGHT, THE POWER IN THE
GAME SHIFTS TO THE JURY.
NINE PEOPLE THAT YOU HAD A HAND
IN VOTING OUT WILL NOW DECIDE
WHO THEY THINK IS MOST WORTHY OF
THE TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR, AND
THE MILLION DOLLARS THAT GOES
WITH IT.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE NIGHT.
TRY TO GET SOME SLEEP.
YOU'RE GOINGS TO NEED TO COME
STRONG TOMORROW.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT FOR YOUR
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WOO.
STUPID, STUPID, STUPID.
I THINK YOU MADE A HORRIFIC
MILLION-DOLLAR DECISION.
I THINK YOU ACTUALLY COULD HAVE
BEATEN ME.
I'M VERY PLEASE WITH THE GAME I
PLAYED.
SOME PEOPLE WILL HATE ME.
SOME PEOPLE WILL APPRECIATE THAT
I'M A FAN AND I PLAYED HARD.
AND I PLAYED TO WIN.
AND IN THE END, I HAD A HELL OF
A TIME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO TELL YOU,
MY MAN.
>> ONE LOVE, MAN.
>> WHAT DID FOR ME TONIGHT IS
MORE THAN I EVER DID FOR YOU, MY
FRIEND.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> ONE LOVE, BRO.
>> ONE LOVE IS RIGHT.
>> FINAL TWO!
WHOOO!
PRIOR TO TRIBAL COUNCIL I WAS
HAVING A REALLY TOUGH TIME.
IT'S NOT AN EASY DECISION TO
MAKE, BUT MY DECISION TONIGHT IS
A BIG POWER MOVE THAT I CAN
FINALLY CLAIM AS MY OWN.
SO WHAT REALLY GOT ME TO LEAN
MORE TOWARDS TAKING TONY WAS
WHAT I THOUGHT THE JURY WOULD
RESPECT.
>> LIKEABILITY ALONE DOESN'T WIN
YOU THE MILLION, BUT NOW YOU
HAVE THAT RESPECT BEHIND IT.
WE BOTH HAVE A SHOT, AND THAT'S
ALL WE WANTED.
>> YEAH, THAT'S IT, MAN.
WE GOT 50-50, BRO.
I KNOW THAT TAKING TONY COULD
JEOPARDIZE MY CHANCES OF WINNING
A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> WHAT YOU DID TONIGHT, BLOWS
EVERYTHING AWAY, BECAUSE I'M
HERE BECAUSE OF YOU NOW.
>> BUT TAKING HIM JUST FELT
RIGHT IN A MARTIAL ARTS
TOURNAMENT, IF I WENT UP AGAINST
SOMEONE WHO WASN'T AS TALENTED
AS I WAS, THAT VICTORY WOULDN'T
BE AS SWEET.
YOU WANT TO GO UP AGAINST
SOMEONE WHO IS JUST AS STRONG,
MAYBE EVEN STRONGER, SO IF YOU
DO WIN, IT'S THAT MUCH MORE
HONORABLE.
>> TREE MAIL, TREE MAIL.
>> TREE MAIL.
>> OH!
WOW, MAN.
>> THIS IS THE BEST TREE MAIL
WE'VE GOT SINCE WE'VE BEEN ON
THIS ISLAND.
LET ME LIFT THIS UP.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU TAKE A LOOK INSIDE.
>> OH!
>> TODAY WE TAKE A WALK TO TREE
MAIL.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
EGGS, CROISSANTS, SAUSAGES,
BACON.
I REALLY AM LOVING LIFE.
>> MAYBE THAT'S BEEF BACON.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN I DON'T
KNOW WHAT IT MEANS.
>> I JUST HEAR MY WIFE SAY STUFF
LIKE THAT.
>> I'M NOT THE BEST CHEF, I'M
NOT A KITCHEN INN THIEWZ
YESTERDAY AT ALL AND NEITHER IS
TONY.
HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO COOK
EGGS.
>> WE'RE GOING TO GET SICK FOR
REAL, MAN.
>> WHAT DO WE DO BEST?
WE EAT.
>> I'M STILL IN "SURVIVOR" MODE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, THERE WAS A
CLUE IN THE BASKET.
I SEE THE CLUE, AND I WENT INTO
MY BASIC INSTINCT.
WOO IS COOKING UP THE FOOD, AND
AS I AM TALKING TO HIM I GRAB
THE CLUE AND PUT IT IN MY POCKET
AND I'M LIKE WHAT COULD THIS BE.
MAYBE IT'S A FREE VOTE.
IT GAVE ME A HINT ABOUT GOING TO
THE BACK OF THE CAMP AND THERE'S
ANOTHER SURPRISE WAITING FOR ME.
SO I SAID, LET ME JUST GO SEE
WHAT THIS IS.
AND IT WAS A MIRROR WITH A
SCALE.
I HOOKED IN THE MIRROR, AND
THANK GOD IT DIDN'T CRACK.
WOW!
OH, MY GOODNESS!
IT SAYS 171.
NOW I'M 150.
21 POUNDS I LOST OUT HERE.
THIS IS SICK.
I CAME OUT HERE NOT KNOWING
ANYTHING ABOUT MAKING FIRES, NOT
KNOWING ANYTHING ABOUT CUTTING
PALM FRONDS.
I NEVER HELD A MASHET NEMY HAND
IN MY LIFE.
I JUST USED MY COMMON SENSE.
>> WOO?
>> WHAT?
>> COME HERE, KID.
I FOUND SOMETHING.
>> THROUGHOUT THIS GAME, TONY
HAD SO MANY NAMES, TONY IN
TROUBLE.
TONE NECHARGE.
TONE IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT.
TONE NECONTROL.
TODAY, I FEEL LIKE I'M TONE
NENEED OF A MILLION DOLLARS.
A MILLION DOLLARS WAS MY MAIN
PRIORITY TO COME OUT HERE.
TO BETTER MY LIFE, BETTER MY
WIFE'S LIFE.
AND ALL MY WIFE WANTS IS A PINK
CHANDELIER FOR MY BABY DAUGHTER
AND SHE MY BABY DAUGHTER'S GOING
TO HAVE A BEAUTIFUL PINK
CHANDELIER WHEN I GET BACK HOME.
>> OH, DAMN!
I LOOK GOOD!
WHOA!
>> I DIDN'T HAVE THE SAME--
>> OH, MAN.
I'M LOOKING FINE, BRO.
LOOK AT MY MUSTACHE!
OH, MY GOSH, BRO.
ONE 62?
NOW I WAY 143.
I'M HERE, I MADE THE FINAL TWO.
IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE.
OH, MAN, I WANT THIS MORE THAN
ANYTHING.
I'M GOING TO GO INTO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, AND I'M GOING TO LET
THE JURY KNOW EXACTLY HOW I FELT
ABOUT THE GAME.
I'M A MARTIAL ARTS INSTRUCTOR,
AND WE ABIDE BY THE FIVE CODES
OF TAIWAN DOUGH-- DISCIPLINE,
INTEGRITY, LOILTD, RESPECT,
HARMONY BETWEEN MIND AND BODY.
I DID A VAL YAPT EFFORT ABIDING
BY THOSE CODES OF CONDUCT
THROUGHOUT THIS GAME, AND NO ONE
CAN QUESTION ME ON THAT.
I'M GOING IN WITH 50% CHANCE OF
WINNING A MILLION DOLLARS.
IT MEANS A JUMP START TO MY
FUTURE, TO START UP MYTAE KWON
DO STUDIO I ALWAYS DREAMED OF,
ENGAGE MY GIRLFRIEND CHRISTINE
AND HELP MY FATHER RETIRE.
MY MOTHER, WHO SUFFERED A HEART
ATTACK, IS DISABLED.
SO I CAN CHANGE THEIR LIVES,UN.
IT'S A BLESSING, MAN.
IT ALL STEMS DOIN TO BEING
POSITIVE, NEVER LOSING HOPE,
STAYING TRUE TO YOURSELF,
BELIEVING IN YOURSELF.
MAN, I'M THIS CLOSE, THIS CLOSE.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF YOUR JURY.
SARAH.
MORGAN.
L.J.
JEREMIAH.
JEFRA.
TASHA.
TRISH.
SPENCER.
AND KASS, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
TONY, WOO, WELCOME TO YOUR FINAL
TONIGHT, THE POWER SHIFTS TO THE
JURY, NINE PEOPLE THAT YOU HAD A
HAND IN VOTING OUT, WILL DECIDE
WHO THEY THINK IS MOST WORTHY OF
THE TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR, AND
THE MILLION DOLLAR CHECK THAT
GOES ALONG WITH IT.
THEY'RE GOING TO ASK YOU TOUGH
QUESTIONS.
YOUR JOB, PERSUADE THEM WITH
COMPELLING ANSWERS.
LET'S GET STARTED.
OPENING STATEMENTS.
TONY, YOU'RE UP.
>> TONIGHT, I KNOW I HAVE A LOT
OF ANSWERS, A LOT OF EXPLAINING
TO DO FOR ALL MY VOTE-OFFS.
I'M HERE TO GIVE YOU GUYS THE
TRUTH.
PRETTY MUCH, YOU ASK ME ANYTHING
YOU WANT.
I WELCOME ALL YOUR QUESTIONS,
AND I'M HERE TO ANSWER THEM
TRUTHFULLY, AND JUST LET YOU ALL
KNOW IT WAS NOTHING EMOTIONAL,
NOTHING PERSONAL.
ALL THE CHOICES I MADE
THROUGHOUT THIS WHOLE GAME WAS
BASED ON STRATEGY AND THAT'S ALL
IT WAS.
I WANT TO THANK WOO FOR GIVING
ME SHOT, OPPORTUNITY TO EXPLAIN
ALL THIS TO YOU GUYS AFTER
REPEATEDLY HEARING IN PREVIOUS
TRIBAL COUNCILS IF I MAKE IT TO
THE END I WIN, AND HE STILL TOOK
A SHOT AND I WANT TO THANK HIM
FOR THAT.
THANKS, MAN.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: WOO, OPENING
STATEMENT.
>> I CAME IN THIS GAME KNOWING
IT'S A GAME OF LIES,
MANIPULATIONS.
IT WAS PROBABLY ONE OF THE
HARDEST CHALLENGES I WOULD HAVE
TO FACE.
BEING A TIQOWN DO INSTRUCTOR, WE
ABIDE BY FIVE COATS OF TAE KWON
DO-- RESPECT, LOILTD, INTEGRITY,
DISCIPLINE, HARM ME BETWEEN MIND
AND BODY.
I'M NOT SAYING I'M A PERFECT
PERSON BUT I DID MY ABSOLUTE
BEST AND PUT FORWARD A VALIANT
EFFORT TO ABIDE BY THOSE CODES
AND CONDUCTS.
WE ALL HAD OUR DOWNS IN THIS
GAME AND YOU HAVE TO PULL
SOMETHING OUT WITHIN YOU TO
INSPIRE, TO MOTIVATE TO YOU KEEP
GOING.
FOR ME, IT WAS THE THE MEMORY OF
MY MOM WHO UNDERWENT A HEART
ATTACK LAST YEAR, UNDERWENT A
MAJOR HEART TRANSPLANT.
SHE WENT THROUGH A GRUELING
RECOVERY.
TO ME SHE WAS A TESTAMENT OF
WHAT WILL POWER, STRENGTH, AND
RESILIENCE WAS ALL ABOUT AND A
CONSTANT REMINDER TO NEVER GIVE
UP, FIGHT EVERY DAY TO SURVIVE.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME AND I
LOOK FORWARD TO ANSWERING ANY
SPECIFIC QUESTIONS YOU GUYS
MIGHT HAVE.
THANKS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY, IN A
MOMENT, YOUR FIRST CHANCE TO
ADDRESS TONY AND WOO.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MOMENT TO THINK
ABOUT WHAT YOU WANT TO SAY.
WE'RE DOWN TO IT, AND I'M JOINED
BY PARVEETY.
PARVEETY IS A WINNER.
ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR PLAYERS,
A LOT OF PEOPLE THINK ONE OF THE
BEST, MYSELF INCLUDED.
I WANTED YOU TO GIVE A LITTLE
INSIGHT.
AFTER 39 DAYS, YOU HAVE A
GIGANTIC TASK THAT YOU HAVE TO
CONVINCE THESE PEOPLE.
HOW BIG A FACTOR IS FATIGUE?
>> IT'S EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE EXHAUSTED.
AT LEAST YOU'RE NOT STARVE
MORE BECAUSE YOU GET THAT NICE
BREAKFAST OF BEEF BACON, OR WHAT
TONY JUST ATE.
IT HELPS A LOT BUT EXHAUSTION
SAY BIG FACTOR.
>> Jeff: WHAT IS THE MISTAKE
PEOPLE MAKE THAT THEY SHOULDN'T
COOR SHOULD DO?
>> I THINK THE BIGGEST MISTAKE
GOING UP AGAINST A JURY, IF
THEY'RE A HOSTILE JURY OR
FRIENDLY JURY IS BEING
DEFENSIVE.
YOU HAVE TO LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
YOU HAVE TO BE VULNERABLE.
AND YOU HAVE TO BE OPEN AND
REALLY STAND BEHIND THE MOVES
THAT YOU MADE.
>> Jeff: WHO DO YOU VOTE FOR
OUT OF THESE TWO?
>> I LOVE WOO --
>> WHO DO YOU VOTE FOR?
>> I WOULD VOTE FOR TONY.
>> Jeff: THERE YOU GO, LOVE
WOO.
VOTE FOR TONY.
THE FINAL Q & A IS NEXT.
THE NEXT TIME SEE YOU, I WILL
HAVE AN URN FILLED WITH A
MILLION DOLLARS.
SHE KNOWS WHAT THAT FEELS LIKE.
ITS THE CONCLUSION TO ONE
ONE OF THE BEST SEASON WE HAD
WELL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY, SOME
OF YOU HAVE WAITED A VERY LONG
TIME TO ADDRESS TONEY AND WOO.
I KNOW YOU HAVE QUESTIONS.
YOU WANT ANSWERS.
YOU ARE SEEKING INFORMATION TO
HELP YOU MAKE A MILLION-DOLLAR
VOTE.
LET'S GET TO IT.
SARAH.
YOU'RE UP.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, YOU GUYS.
TONY, WHEN YOU SWORE TO ME THAT
YOU WOULD NEVER WRITE MY NAME
DOWN ON YOUR BADGE, AND I SWORE
THEY WOULD NEVER WRITE YOUR NAME
DOWN ON MY BANL, MY BADGE MEANS
SOMETHING TO ME.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOURS
MEANS TO YOU, BUT YOU BROKE YOUR
PROMISE.
AND I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN
WRITE YOUR NAME DOWN TONIGHT.
WOO.
MY QUESTION FOR YOU IF YOU AND I
FLIP-FLOP PLACES, AND I PLAYED
THE EXACT GAME YOU PLAYED, WHO
WOULD YOU VOTE FOR, ME OR TONY?
>> I MEAN, UNDER THE
CIRCUMSTANCES, WITHOUT-- IF YOU
PLAYED WITHOUT ANY HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, I WOULD GIVE YOU
A LOT OF CREDIT FOR MAKING IT
THROUGH.
I WOULD GIVE YOU A LOT OF
RESPECT, AND I WOULD VOTE FOR
YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: THANKS, SARAH.
JEFRA.
>> I'M NOT BITTER, AND I WANT TO
BE FAIR, BUT, TONY, I WANT YOU
TO OWN YOUR GAME.
I WANT YOU TO LOOK ME IN THE
EYES FOR THE FIRST TIME AND OWN
THE FACT THAT YOU BACKSTABBED
ALMOST EVERYBODY ON THIS JURY,
THAT YOU HAD NO LOYALTY TO ANY
OF YOU, THAT YOU LOOKED ME IN
THE EYE THE DAY YOU VOTED ME
OUT, TOLD ME I WAS SAFE.
I GET IT.
BUT I WANT YOU TO OWN IT, AND I
WANT YOU TO ADMIT IT, AND THE
SECOND YOU START GIVING ME B.S.
ANSWERS IS THE SECOND I WILL
WRITE A "W"DOWN SO FAST.
>> OWN EVERYTHING, JEFRA.
I DIDN'T BLACKSTAB YOU.
YOU PLANNED ON BLINDSIDING ME.
YOU TALKED TO SPENCER AND TASHA
AND JEREMIAH.
AND YOU WANTED TO BLINDSIDE
TONEY AND THAT WAS THE PLAN AND
I WENT TO MY ALLIANCE AND TOLD
THEM JEFRA HAS FLIPPED AND HAD
INCREDIBLE INFORMATION--
>> YOU VOTED ME OUT.
I GET IT.
I WANT YOU TO OWN YOUR GAME.
>> I DIDN'T BACKSTAB YOU.
>> I WASN'T GOING TO FLIP ON YOU
AND IF I WANTED TO I WOULD HAVE
DONE IT THE VOTE BEFORE.
I DECIDED TO STICK WITH YOU.
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
ENT YOU TO OWN THE GAME AND
ADMIT YOU WERE THE VILLAIN.
>> I AM OWNING IT JEFRA, I AM.
>> YOU THINK YOU WERE THE
VILLAIN, THE WAY YOU TREATED
THIS JURY.
>> YES, HALF AND HALF, HALF
VILLAIN, HALF GOOD PLAYER.
I WAS A GOOD PLAYER.
I WASN'T A VILLAIN.
I WAS DOING STRATEGIC MOVES TO
SAVE MYSELF.
>> OKAY THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: THANKS, JEFRA.
MORGAN.
>> HI, GENTLEMEN.
SO, TONY, I JUST WANT TO START
OFF WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW, I STARTED OUT THIS
GAME ON THE BEAUTY TRIBE, WHICH
I FOUND PRETTY FITTING TO BEING,
YOU KNOW, A YOUNG AND ATTRACTIVE
WOMAN.
I KNOW HOW TO KEEP A MAN IN MY
BACKPOCKET, AND I THINK IT'S
SORT OF A SKILL.
YOU KEPT MEN IN YOUR BACK
POCKET.
AND YOU DID IT WITHOUT EVEN
HAVING BREASTS.
SO HOW DID YOU DO IT?
I JUST WANT TO KNOW.
HOW DID YOU GET THESE MEN TO
JUST FOLLOW YOU?
>> I WAS GENUINE AT CAMP,
OFFERING MY LAST SIP OF WATER TO
PEOPLE THAT NEEDED IT.
OFFERING MY LAST SEA SHELL OF
RICE THAT NEEDED IT.
THAT WAS THE GENUINE ME.
MY GAME PLAY WAS A DIFFERENT
STORY.
THE STRATEGIES I DID WAS TO
BETTER MYSELF IN THE GAME AND
DID THE BEST I CAN.
SOMEONE LIKE WOO WAS LOYAL TO ME
AND I APPRECIATED HIM FOR
EVERYTHING HE DID BE AND THAT'S
HOW HE STAYED WITH ME THE WHOLE
TIME.
>> WOO, I JUST HAVE A STATEMENT
FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, LAST NIGHT, YOU MADE A
HUGE DECISION TAKING TONY OVER
KASS.
AND I JUST HAVE TO SAY, YOU
KNOW, I RESPECT THAT.
YOU KNOW, YOU CHOSE A PLAYER
THAT DESERVED TO BE HERE TONIGHT
OVER, YOU KNOW, JUST A GOAT
THAT'S MAYBE NOT WORTHY OF
SITTING THERE WITH YOU TWO.
AND I JUST WANT YOU TON THAT I'M
TAKING THAT INTO HUGE
CONSIDERATION.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: JEREMIAH.
>> WHAT'S UP?
TONY, TO ME, YOUR BIGGEST MOVE
IN THIS GAME IS YOU SWEAR ON
YOUR SO-CALLED WIFE AND KID.
IF YOU DO HAVE A WIFE AND KID,
AND YOU SWORE ON THEIR LIVES AND
BREAKING PROMISES, WHERE WHERE
I'M FROM THAT'S A 100%
GRADE-A( BLEEP ) RIGHT THERE.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE A WIFE AND KID
YOU REALLY DIDN'T BREAK
ANYTHING.
I HAVE TO SAY THAT WAS A PRETTY
MUCH BRILLIANT AND GREAT MOVE
SPRIP A YES OR NO QUESTION RIGHT
HERE BETWEEN ME AND YOU, NO B.S.
DO YOU HAVE A WIFE AND BABY?
>> ABSOLUTE DO AND I LOVE THEM.
>> YOU HAVE A WIFE AND BABY?
>> YES, I DO.
>> FROM WHERE I'M FROM, WHEN
PEOPLE PROMISE AND SWEAR ON
THEIR WIFE AND KID AND THEY
BREAK THESE PROMISES--
>> I CAN EXPLAEN SOMETHING TO
YOU.
>> THAT'S PATHETIC.
>> I CAN EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO
YOU OR NOT?
>> THAT'S IT, BRO, THAT'S IT.
WOO I JUST FOUND OUT HE'S LIED
TO US ALL.
THIS IS YOUR TIME TO PROVE,
DUDE, I MEAN, DID YOU WANT TO BE
A MILLIONAIRE?
I'VE GOT TO KNOW, MAN.
>> ABSOLUTELY, JEREMIAH.
I CAME HERE WITH MY MAIN
INCLINATION OF DEFINITELY BEING
THE SOLE SURVIVOR, AND WANTING
TO WIN THE MILLION DOLLARS.
AND I DEFINITELY WANT TO WIN
THAT MILLION DOLLARS, NO DOUBT,
JEREMIAH.
>> Jeff: THANKS, JEREMIAH.
TASHA.
>> TONY, YOU MANAGED TO KEEP A
LOYAL ALLIANCE OF PEOPLE DESPITE
YOUR REPEATED LIES AND
DISLOYALTY TO THEM.
CAN YOU ARTICULATE TO ME HOW YOU
MANAGED TO DO THAT?
>> ANOTHER FOR EVERY VOTE-OFF
THAT I DID, I EXPLAINED TO MY
ALLIANCE WHY I DID IT.
SO NERVE MY ALLIANCE SAW THE
ONLY TIME I WOULD BREAK MY
PROMISE TO YOU IS IF YOU BROKE
IT TO ME FIRST.
THE ONLY PERSON I BROKE MY
PROMISE TO REGRETFULLY WAS
TRISH.
SHE NEVER DID ANYTHING.
SHE NEVER WENT BEHIND MY BACK TO
BACKSTAB ME.
SHE WOULD HAVE STAYED LOYAL TO
ME TO THE END.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE I FEEL DIDN'T
BREAK HER PROMISE TO ME FIRST.
I BROKE IT FIRST.
>> THANK YOU.
WOO, CONGRATULATIONS.
MY QUESTION FOR YOU IS HOW DID
YOU CHOOSE TO ALIGN WITH TONY
VERSUS ANYONE ELSE THAT WAS IN
YOUR ALLIANCE, STRATEGICALLY?
>> THE MAJORITY OF THIS GAME,
TONY AND I WERE NOT CLOSE.
HE DIDN'T TRUST ME.
HE THOUGHT I WAS A WEASEL.
DAY ONE.
IT WASN'T UNTIL THAT SOLANA 5
THAT HE REALLY TRUSTED ME GOING
INTO THE MERGE.
I WAS THE ODD MAN OUT OUT OF OUR
NEW SOLANA 5.
I KNEW IF THE NEXT PERSON WERE
TO GO IN OUR 5 IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN ME.
I MANAGED TO ADAPT AND MOLD
MYSELF, EVEN THOUGH I KNEW I WAS
ODD MAN OUT.
>> OKAY, THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: THANKS, TASHA.
L.J.
>> I CAN SPEAK.
I NEED TO KNOW WITH YOU, TONY,
LIKE, WHO ARE YOU?
LIKE, DID YOU BRING YOU OR ARE
YOU JUST LIVING, YOU KNOW, A
FANTASY WORLD AND PLAYING A
GAME?
>> WELL, IT DEPEND ON WHETHER
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE GAME.
AS FAR AS YOU'RE CONCERNED,
WILLING, I SEEN, YOU I WAS
PETRIFIED OF YOU.
I KNEW HOW STRATEGIC YOU WERE, I
WAS LOOKING FOR THE QUICKEST
EXCUSE I COULD FIND BECAUSE I
WAS TERRIFIED OF YOU.
I YOU SAID MAYBE WE NEED TO GET
WOO OUT.
I WAS LIKE YES, HE WAS WILLING
TO BRECK HAZE PROMISE AND NOW I
CAN BREAK MINE.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT AND I
RESPECT THAT, HOWEVER, YOU
PLAYED ME.
>> I HAVE TO LIE L.J. IN THE
GAPE.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> AND I USED THAT AS AN EXCUSE.
OH, L.J. WANTED TO VOTE YOU OUT
FIRST.
L.J. WAS WILLING TO MAKE A
PROMISE HE MADE.
GUESS WHAT?
LET'S BREAK THE PROMISE TO HIM.
>> ALL RIGHT, I HAVE NOTHING
MORE.
>> Jeff: KASS, YOU'RE UP.
>> WOO, LAST NIGHT, YOU BECAME
THE BOSS.
YOU HAD THE NECKLACE.
YOU USURPED THE POWER OF TONY
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
WHY ON EARTH DID YOU NOT CUT THE
HEAD OF THE DRAGON OFF?
THE INTEGRITY OF GAME IS TO HAVE
THE WINNER MAKE THE RIGHT MOVES.
YOU DIDN'T MAKE A MOVE WHEN YOU
COULD HAVE THAT WOULD HAVE WON
YOU A MILLION DOLLARS.
>> YOU KNOW, LAST NIGHT, I HAD A
HUGE RESPONSIBILITY ON MY HAND
FOR ME AND MY FIELD OF STUDIES,
I'M A MAN WHO IS TRYING TO BE
HONORABLE, NO MATTER WHAT.
A MILLION DOLLARS MEANS A WHOLE
BUNCH TO ME.
BUT I FELT THAT MY PART TO BRING
ALONG SOMEONE THAT DESERVED TO
BE HERE WOULD GIVE ME POINT FROM
THE JURY.
>> YOU BROUGHT SOMEONE WHO
DESERVED IT MORE THAN YOU TO GET
POINTS FOR YOURSELF?
>> WE'RE ALL DESERVING, KASS.
BUT BETWEEN THE TWO OF YOU, I
DIDN'T FEEL LIKE YOU DESERVED TO
SIT HERE NEXT TO ME BUT TONY DID
DID.
>> OKAY.
I'M GOOD, I THINK.
>> Jeff: THANKS, KASS.
TRISH.
>> HI, GUYS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WOO, I HAVE JUST ONE QUESTION
FOR YOU.
WAS IT YOUR IDEA OR WAS IT
TONY'S IDEA TO BLINDSIDE ME?
>> IT WAS MY IDEA.
>> WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO DO
THAT?
YOU HAVE A GREAT REPUTATION WITH
THE JURY.
YOU'RE A SWEETHEART.
I FELT THAT WE WOULDN'T HAVE A
SHOT WITH YOU AT THE FINAL
THREE.
>> THAT'S FAIR ENOUGH.
THANK YOU FOR THE COMPLIMENT.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
TONY, WHEN I FIRST SHOWED UP,
YOU AND I FIRST DAY, BECAME THE
BEST OF BUDDIES.
AND INSTANT FRIEND.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE STARTED TO SHARE INTIMATE
STORIES.
NOW YOU SIT HERE NOW, AND YOU
WOULD NOT BE SITTING THERE IF I
DIDN'T HAVE A BIG PART IN IT.
BECAUSE NOBODY HERE EVER FOR ONE
SECOND TRUSTED YOU.
THEY TRUSTED ME.
AND I HAD TO CONVINCE THEM ALL
TO TRUST ME TO TRUST YOU.
AND I SPENT THE ENTIRE GAME
PUTTING OUT LITTLE FLAMES FOR
TONY.
SO YOU COULD SIT THERE.
AND YOU CAME TO ME IN YOUR
PARANOIA AND YOU SAID, "I'M
TELLING YOU, MAN, I'M TELLING
YOU, SOMETHING'S GOING WRONG
HERE.
OF I SAID, "TONY TAKE A CHILL
PILL.
RELAX.
I'M HERE FOR YOU.
I'M NEVER GOING TO LEAVE YOU."
AND YOU SAID, "I NEED TON THAT
FOR A FACT."
I SAID DON'T BE SWEARING ON YOUR
MOTHER AND KID.
DID YOU THAT FOR EVERYBODY ELSE.
FIND SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
AND YOU LOOKED RIGHT AT ME AND
SAID TO ME AND SAID I WILL SWEAR
ON MY FATHER'S GRAVE.
I'VE LOST TWO SIBLINGS.
AND THOSE TWO LOSSES HAVE PUT
TWO HOLES IN MY HEART THAT COULD
NEVER, EVER BE REPAIRED.
I WOULD NEVER, EVER, EVER HAVE
GONE BACK ON THE PROMISE OF MY
BROTHERS.
NOT TODAY, NOT TOMORROW.
NOT FOR 100 MILLION DOLLARS, NOT
FOR ANYTHING.
I HAVE ONE MILLION-DOLLAR
QUESTION FOR YOU THAT I WANT YOU
TO ANSWER TO YOUR MOTHER, TO
YOUR WIFE, MARIS ATO YOUR
DAUGHTER, AN STAISHIA.
WAS IT WORTH IT TO YOU FOR A
MILLION DOLLARS TO SACRIFICE
YOUR OWN FATHER TO GET YOU HERE?
WAS THAT WORTH IT TO YOU?
>> TRISH, I WAS OUTNUMBERED WHEN
WOO CAME UP TO SMEE HE HAD
SPENCE EAR?
>>
>> I ASKED YOU A QUESTION.
I DON'T WANT EXCUSES.
I'M SAYING TO YOU, HEART TO
HEART, FRIEND TO FRIEND, HUMAN
BEING TO HUMAN BEING.
ANSWER THE QUESTION.
IS IT WORTH IT TO YOU TO BE
HERE, TO PLAY A GAME, FOR A
MILLION DOLLARS ON YOUR FATHER'S
SOUL AND MEMORY?
YES OR NO.
IT'S A MILLION-DOLLAR QUESTION.
>> YES.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: SPENCER.
>> LET'S DO THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
WOO, WHEN I LOOK AT YOUR GAME, I
CAN'T HELP BUT MAKE THIS
COMPARISON BETWEEN YOUR
STRATEGIC PLAY AND THE BEHAVIOR
OF A DOG.
I MEAN, TONY WAS LIKE YOUR
MASTER.
WHEN HE SAID, "SIT," YOU SAT.
WHEN HE SAID THE WORD, YOU WENT
AND PLAYED FETCH.
THE L.J. VOTE.
THE JEFRA BLINDSIDE.
EVEN IN CAMP LIFE, YOU WERE IN
HIS POCKET 24/7.
WHEN IT CAME DOWN TO YOU HAVING
AN OPPORTUNITY TO TAKE ONE OF
THE BIGGEST GOATS IN SURVIVOR
HISTORY TO THE END, YOU DID WHAT
A GOOD DOG WOULD DO AND STAYED
LOYAL TO YOUR OWNER, AND IS
THERE ANYTHING YOU CAN SAY TO ME
TO CONVINCE ME THAT THIS ANALOGY
DISAPPOINT MAKE SENSE?
FOR SOMEONE LIKE YOU WHO HAS
BEEN A STUDENT OF THE GAME,
SOMEONE WHO APPRECIATES THE
GAME, CAN YOU RESPECT ME IF I
TOOK A GOAT LIKE KASS TO THE
FINALS?
>> YES, AS A STUDENT OF THE
GAME, I WOULD EXPECT YOU TO TAKE
A GOAT TO THE FINALS.
>> BUT FOR ME, I'M A DIFFERENT
STUDENT, I GUESS.
I WANTED TO TAKE SOMEONE WHO
DESERVED TO GO.
>> OKAY, THANKS.
TONY, I DON'T NEED TO ASK YOU
ANY QUESTIONS.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU ALL.
LOVE HIM OR HATE HIM, TONY
PLAYED HIS ASS OFF OUT HERE.
WOO TRIES TO EXCUSE HIS PASSIVE
PLAY ON NOT HAVING IDOLS AND
TONE FINDING THREE IDOLS.
WHY DO YOU THINK TONY FOUND
THREE IDOLS?
IT'S BECAUSE HE LOOKED MORE THAN
EVERYONE ELSE COMBINED.
TONY WAS BEHIND EVERY GREAT
STRATEGIC DECISION.
HE BLINDED HIS ALLIANCE TO WHAT
WAS GOING ON AROUND HIM IN THE
GAME.
LIKE A PUPPET MASTER.
HE TOOK A SLEW OF GOATS DEEP.
PUT SOME ON THE JURY.
HE TOOK ONE TO THE END.
TONY PLAYED WITH A VEROCITY.
THIS GAME VERY RARELY DOES SEE.
AND YOU PUT PEN TO PARCHMENT
TONIGHT, VOTE FOR THE ONLY GUY
SITTING THERE THAT ACTUALLY
PLAYED THIS GAME AND PLAYED IT
IN A WAY THAT HONORS IT.
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU TWO.
39 DAYS OUT HERE ISN'T EASY.
THANKS.
>> THANKS, SPENCER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, A VERY
TOUGH FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BUT YOU TWO, TONY AND WOO, YOU
WEATHERED IT.
YOUR WORK IS DONE.
THE ONLY THING LEFT TO DO IS
VOTE.
YOU HAVE ALL THE INFORMATION
YOU'RE GOING TO GET TO MAKE A
MILLION-DOLLAR VOTE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO TAKE IT ALL IN, AND THEN
WE'LL VOTE.
ALLRIGHT JURY IT
IS TIME TO VOTE.
TONIGHT, ARE YOU VOTING FOR A
WINNER.
THIS IS A MILLION DOLLAR VOTE.
IT IS TONY OR WOO.
THE LAST TIME, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
SARAH, YOU'RE UP.
>> I WROTE YOUR NAME DOWN MANY
TIMES DURING THE GAME.
IT WAS A COMPLIMENT THEN.
IT IS DEFINITELY A COMPLIMENT
NOW.
WELL DONE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO GET THE
VOTES.
JURY, TONY, WOO, THANK YOU FOR
ANOTHER GREAT SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR.
I WILL TAKE THESE, SEE YOU BACK
IN THE UNITED STATES FOR THE
READING OF THE VOTES.
GOOD JOB.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT!
THANK YOU!
IT'S BEEN A FUN NIGHT.
HAVE A SEAT.
THIS HAS BEEN FUN.
I'VE LIKED BEING LIVE WITH YOU
GUYS.
THE ENERGY IN HERE IS CRAZY.
ALL RIGHT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
I WANT TO SAY SOMETHING.
TONY, WOO, JURY, AND THIS GOES
FOR THE NONJURY AS WELL.
I CANNOT THINK OF ANOTHER SEASON
IN WHICH MORE PEOPLE CAME TO
PLAY, MEANING YOU PLAYED TO WIN.
AND I THINK THAT IS WHY THIS HAS
BEEN ONE OF OUR VERY BEST
SEASONS BECAUSE THAT IS HOW
"SURVIVOR" IS MEANT TO BE
PLAYED.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
AND THIS IS HOW "SURVIVOR" IS
MEANT TO END, WITH A VOTE.
THERE ARE NINE VOTES.
IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
IT TAKES FIVE TO WIN.
THESE ARE VOTES FOR A WINNER.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
FIRST VOTE, TONY.
WOO.
ONE VOTE TONY, ONE VOTE WOO.
TONY.
TWO VOTES TONY, ONE VOTE WOO.
THREE VOTES TONY, ONE VOTE WOO.
TONY.
FOUR VOTES TONY, ONE VOTE WOO.
THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR:
CAGAYAN," TONY.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
( CHEERS )
>> Jeff: GO SEE YOUR FAMILY.
GO DOWN THERE.
YOU DID IT!
IT'S OVER!
28 SEASONS.
TONY'S WON.
ONE OF THE BEST SEASONS.
ONE OF THE BEST CASTES OF ALL
TIME.
DEFINITELY SOME UNFINISHED
BUSINESS TO DEAL WITH.
WE HAVE EVERYBODY HERE.
PLUS A "SURVIVOR" FIRST A PUBLIC
APOLOGY FROM ME AND IT HAS TO DO
WITH SPENCER.
AND THE BIG QUESTION, DID WOO
MAKE A MILLION-DOLLAR MISTAKE?
IN CHOOSING THIS GUY, TONY?
WE'LL POLL THE JURY.
PLUS, TYLER PERRY, THE MAN
RESPONSIBLE FOR THE IDOL WITH
DIFFERENT POWERS IS HERE.
WE'RE LIVE STILL IN THE LOS
ANGELES, THE REUNION SHOW IS
NEXT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )