>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I'D LIKE TO GIVE IT TO LJ.
>> I'D LIKE TO COVER TONY'S ASS,
MYSELF.
>> Jeff: AFTER L.J. AND TONY
SACRIFICED THEIR IDOLS FOR EACH
OTHER--
>> WHO FLIPPED?
>> KASS.
>> Jeff: AND KASS FLIPPED.
>> KASS, ZERO CHANCE OF WINNING
THE GAME.
>> Jeff: THE POWER SHIFTED TO
EYE NEW MAJORITY ALLIANCE LED BY
L.J. AND TONY.
>> AS FAR AS NUMBERS, MY
ALLIANCE IS IN THE POWER
POSITION RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: WITH THE HIERARCHY OF
POWER INTACT, EVERYONE'S FOCUS
SHIFTED TO FINDING HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOLS.
>> IS EVERYONE LOOKING AT THIS
POINT?
>> EVERYBODY.
>> THERE'S A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, SPECIAL POWERS, AROUND
CAMP.
>> Jeff: FORTUNATELY, FOR
SPENCER, HE FOUND ONE, THOUGH IS
WASN'T THE IDOL WITH DIFFERENT
POWERS.
>> IT'S JUST THE PLAIN, OLD IDOL
BUT I BOUGHT MYSELF A LOT OF
TIME POTENTIALLY.
>> Jeff: AND AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE HE OUTLASTED ALL THE
REST.
SPENCER WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL, MAT JORT
ALLIANCE WAS WORRIED ABOUT A
POSSIBLE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> LOOK AT MORGAN, SHE DOES
NOTHING BUT SLEEP.
THEY HAVE AN IDOL, THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO SHARE IT WITH HER.
>> SHE DOES NEED TO GO.
>> Jeff: AND AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL-- THAT'S FOUR VOTES
TONY, FIVE VOTES MORGAN, ONE
VOTE LEFT.
THEY STUCK WITH THE SAFE VOTE.
MORGAN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NINE ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
TELL ME HOW IT'S A COMPLIMENT
THAT TWO TIMES IN A ROW YOU GUYS
ARE TRYING TO GET ME OUT.
JUST HUMOR ME.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE A BIG THREAT,
MAN.
>> I APPRECIATE IT MAN KNOW
WHY WE VOTED OFF MORGAN TODAY?
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT WORTHY OF
BEING HERE ANY MORE DAYS.
THAT'S WHY JEREMIAH AND TASH
STAYED.
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT WORTHY OF
PLAYING THIS GAME.
TWO TIMES IN A ROW YOU WANT TO
GET ME OUT.
>> WE WANT A FIGHTING CHANCE.
>> WHEN JEFF TURNED OVER THAT
CARD AND IT SAID, TONY I
PROBABLY POOPED ON MYSELF.
I WASN'T EXPECTING TO SEE MY
NAME.
I'M A 40-YEAR-OLD BALD OLD MAN.
YOU HAVE WOO WHO IS YOUNGER AND
MORE ATHLETIC.
WHY AM I A THREAT?
WHY IS EVERYBODY TRYING TO GET
ME OUT?
YOU COULD HAVE PITCHED THAT TO
US, TOO.
SAID,UN WHAT GUYS WE'RE WILLING
TO VOTE HER OUT.
>> IF YOU WOULD HAVE ASKED US
TO, I WOULD HAVE VOTED FOR
MORGAN.
>> YOU COULD HAVE APPROACHED YOU
SAID US.
>> WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
WE DON'T NEED YOUR VOTES.
YOU COULD HAVE SAID SPARE ME,
SOFTWARE ME, WE WORK HARD AROUND
HERE.
LET'S GET RID OF THIS USELESS
LOAD.
>> GOT IT.
>> BUT I APPRECIATE THE
COMPLIMENT.
HERE WE ARE AGAIN, SIX AGAIN
THREE, BUT IT IS NEVER THAT EASY
BECAUSE WE HAVE SITTING DUCKS.
I'M NOT GOING TO SIT THERE AND
MAKE A FOOL OUT OF MYSELF.
IT'S DEFINITELY NOT GOING TO
COME FOR SOME OF THEM.
YOU KNOW, THAT THEY PUT HIS NAME
DOWN.
>> YEAH, HE'S PISSED.
IT'S HIS WAY OF DEALING WITH IT.
HE WAS PISSED.
>> HE WAS.
I'M SURE THAT MADE HIM REALLY
PARANOID.
>> HUTHAT ANXIETY, YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN?
HE WAS LAUGHING ABOUT IT, BUT,
Y, IT DIDN'T FEEL GOOD MAN, IT
DIDN'T FEEL GOOD.
IS HE NOW GOING TO BE ON
SCRAMBLE MODE?
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
I THINK A LOT OF THE TROUBLE IN
THIS GAME COMES FROM PEOPLE
START GETTING PARNOIRKD PEOPLE
START GETTING IMPATIENT.
TONY DEFINITELY HAS SOME
PARANOIA AND O.C.D. STUFF.
HE SPINS A LOT.
HIS BRAIN IS GOING ALL THE TIME.
THIS IS A GAME OF PATIENCE.
HOPEFULLY HE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING
STUPID.
>> I COULDN'T SLEEP, MAN.
>> YOUR MIND KEEP CRANKING?
>> YEAH, MAN.
MY NAME IS ALWAYS COMING UP
THIS, MAN.
MY NAME IS ALWAYS COMING UP ON
THE BLOCK, BRO.
THIS IS WHERE PEOPLE START TO
PANIC, PEOPLE START SAYING LIES,
PEOPLE CAPTAIN BELIEVE EACH
OTHER.
LOOKING AT L.J. IS LIKE LOOKING
AT MYSELF IN THE MIRROR-- HE'S
SHARP, HE'S KEEPING HIMSELF TWO,
THREE STEPS AHEAD.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE L.J. GONE,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE THE BAD
ONE GETTING RID OF L.J. BECAUSE
SHE MY ALLIANCE.
WE'RE TIGHT AND HE TRUST MEAS
100%.
I HAVE TO TRY TO TRICK L.J. TO
MAKE HIM BREAK A PROMISE HE MADE
TO ONE OF OUR SIX.
ONCE HE DOES THAT, THAT'S OUR
SAFE WAY OUT.
I AM NOT ONLY LEADING THE HORSE
TO THE WATER.
I'M GOING TO MAKE THE HORSE
DRINK THE WATER.
>> HERE'S THE THING, I KNOW YOU
DON'T WANT TO BREAK PROMISES,
BUT IT MIGHT HAVE TO-- IF HE'S
HOLDING IT AND HE KNOWS--
>> HE'S GOT IT, MAN, HE'S GOT
IT.
>> THEN HE'S GOING TO PLAY IT
WHEN HE THINKS HE'S GONE.
>> AND I'M HOPING HE DOESN'T GET
ONE OF US OR SOMEBODY OUT NOW.
>> UP TO THE GET RID OF HIM NOW?
>> OH, MAN.
NO, NO, I'M JUST--
>> IF IT SETTLES YOUR HEAD.
I'M TELLING L.J. I'M VERY
NERVOUS ABOUT WOO HAVING AN IDOL
BUT IT'S NOT TRUE.
L.J. PROPOSED TO ME LET'S
BLINDED SIDE WOO.
I'M GOING TO TELL PEOPLE YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S THINKING.
HE'S QUIET AND SNEAKY AND THAT'S
MORE SCARY THAN A PERSON LIKE
ME.
I'M IN YOUR FACE.
L.J. ON THE OTHER HAND HAS BEEN
THINKING ABOUT ALL YOU GUYS
SINCE DAY ONE BEHIND YOUR BACKS
AND YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ABOUT
IT.
THAT'S WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
I HAVE TO PIN EVERYBODY AGAINST
L.J.
>> TREE MAIL!
>> OKAY, DONT SANDED BAG THIS
ONE.
WHEN A REVITALIZING SENSATION.
BOUNCE BACK INTO COMPETING SHAPE
WITH NOURISHMENT AND
REJUVENATION.
SPA DA?
>> SPA DAY.
>> I WAS JUST THINKING OF HOW IS
NICE THAT WOULD FEEL.
>> TODAY WE GET TREE MAIL AND IT
SAYS IT'S GOING TO BE A REWARD
CHALLENGE.
WHEN YOU GO AWAY FAIR REWARD AND
GET PAMPERED AND PEOPLE GET
SENSITIVE AND EMOTIONS COME OUT,
THEY MIGHT FORM BONDS.
THERE'S POSSIBILITYES OF TALK
THERE.
THERE'S POSSIBILITYES OF
STRATEGIES BEING MENTIONED AND
SCENARIOS AND IT'S VERY SCARY
AND THAT'S WHY I WANT TO WIN
THIS CHALLENGE.
IF ANYONE IS STRATEGIZING AND
COMING UP WITH PLANS, IT'S GOING
TO BE ME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'LL VIED DWOOID
INTO THREE TEAMS OF THREE.
ON MY GO YOU'LL THROW A ROPE
THROUGH A RING, RELEASING SANDED
BAGS.
YOU'LL THEN THROW THE SANDBAGS
AS FAR AS YOU CAN THROUGH A NET
TUNNEL.
ONCE YOU WORK TOGETHER TO
MANEUVER THEM ALL THE WAY
THROUGH, ONE TRIBE MEMBER WILL
BOUNCE THE SANDBAGS OFF A
TRAMPOLINE, ATTEMPTING TO LAND
THEM INTO A SERIES OF
PACIFICETS.
THE FIRST TEAM TO GET ONE
SANDBAG IN EACH OF THE FIVE
BASKETS WINS REWARD.
WANT TON WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR 23 DAYS YOU'VE
BEEN SLEEPING ON BAM BOORKS
PUTTING YOUR BODY THROUGH
UNUSUAL PHYSICAL DEMANDS, AND
THE ONLY THING CLOSE TO HYGIENE
IS RINSING OFF IN THE RAIN.
SO TODAY, THE WINNING TEAM WILL
ENJOY A "SURVIVOR" SPA REWARD.
YOU'LL TAKE A SHOWER, A REAL
SHOWER.
SHOWER-- SHAMPOO, SOAP.
YOU'LL THEN HAVE A MASSAGE, WORK
OUT ALL THOSE ACHES AND PAINS.
YOU WILL THEN HAVE A SPA LURCH--
CHICKEN WRAPS, SPRING ROLLS.
FRESH, COOL, TROPICAL COCKTAILS,
JUST WHAT YOU NEED TO REJIEWF 98
YOUR MIND AND YOUR BODY FOR
THESE LAST 16 DAYS OUT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO DRAW
FOR TEAMS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR THREE
TEAMS.
JEFRA, TRISH, AND L.J.
KASS, TASHA AND WOO.
AND SPENCER, TONY, AND JEREMIAH.
BIG, REJUVENATION REWARD ON THE
LINE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
JEREMIAH, TASHA, AND L.J.
TOSSING THE ROPE.
YOU'RE TRYING TO LOOP IT AROUND
THAT HOOP.
ONCE YOU DO, THAT WILL RELEASE
THE SANDBAGS.
JEREMIAH HAS IT ON HIS SECOND
TOSS.
EARLY LEAD FOR GEMAY, SPENCER,
AND TONY.
JEREMIAH IS ALSO GOING TO BE THE
ONE THROWING THE SANDBAGS.
YOU HAVE TO GO GET IT.
>> COME ON, L.J., YOU KNOT THIS,
BABY.
>> Jeff: A LITTLE LEARNING
CURVE TO THIS LIKE MOST
CHALLENGES.
YOU HAVE TO THROW THOSE SANDBAGS
AS FAR AS YOU CAN THROUGH THE
NET.
L.J. HAS IT THROUGH THE HOOP.
AND RELEASES THE SANDBAGS.
L.J., JEFRA, AND TRISH NOW
MOVING ON TO THE SECOND PHASE.
IT IS WOO, TASHA, AND KASS
BRINGING UP THE REAR.
THERE WOO HAS IT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
AND HE RELEASES THE SANDBAGS.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO GET THOSE BAGS
THROUGH THE TUNNEL.
>> YOU GOT IT.
WE'RE IN IT.
>> IS THAT IT?
>> LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: GEMAY HAS ALL THE
SABD BAGS THROUGH.
THE ONES YOU DIDN'T GET THROUGH,
YOU'VE NOW GOT TO WORK THROUGH.
WOO NOW GETTING A HANG OF IT.
L.J., I DON'T THINK HE MISSED
ONE.
MADE UP A LOT OF TIME FOR THE
OWNER TEAM.
>> HERE GU, LAST ONE.
>> Jeff:
>> Jeff: WOO IS STILL TOSSING
THEM THROUGH.
THERE IT IS, GO.
THE NEXT PHASE IS WORKING THEM
ALL THE WAY THROUGH WILL THE
TUNNEL.
THIS REQUIRES A LOT OF TEAM
WORK.
GREEN STILL WITH A PIT OF A
LEAD.
ORANGE RIGHT BEHIND THEM.
>> PUT YOUR FINGERS THROUGH.
>> GOT IT.
>> Jeff: JEREMIAH, TONY, AND
SPENCER HAVE ALL 20 OF THEIR
SANDBAGS.
LOAD THEM IN THE BASKET, NOW
START BOUNCING THEM OFF THE
TRAMP LEAP.
TONY ISING IF TO BE DOING THE
BOUNCING.
WOO, TASHA, AND KASS STILL WORK
THE BAGS THROUGH.
TONY LAND HIS FIRST ONE.
>> NICE!
>> Jeff: TONE LAND A SECOND
ONE.
>> TONY LAND A THIRD ONE!
THREE IN A ROW FOR TONY.
THE OWNER TEAM HAS ALL 20 OF
THEIR SANDBAGS.
JEFRA NOW GOING TO START
BOUNCING.
>> RETRIEVE, RETRIEVE, RETRIEVE.
>> Jeff: GREEN TEAM WITH A BIG
LEAD RIGHT NOW.
PURPLE TEAM NOW HAS ALL 20 OF
THEIR BAGS.
WOO IS NOW BOUNCING.
EVERYBODY IS NOW BOUNCING
SANDBAGS OFF THE TRAMPOLINE.
AND TONY WITH THE FOURTH BAG.
>> ONE MORE, ONE MORE.
>> Jeff: TONY NEED ONE MORE
AND HE DISW IT.
TONY, JEREMIAH AND SPENCER WIN
REWARD, SPA DAY.
>> NICE JOB.
>> GOOD TRY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SPENCER
TONY,
JEREMIAH, NICE DAY IN FOR YOU.
FIRST YOU GET CLEAN WITH A NICE
SHOWER.
THEN A NICE MASSAGE, AND THEN A.
GRAB YOUR STUFF. OUT.
ENJOY THE AFTERNOON.
TRISH, JEFRA, L.J., KASS, WOO,
TASHA, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> WINNING A REWARD SOMETIMES
CAN BE VERY CRUCIAL TO THE GAME
I'M GOING TO TALK TO SPENCER AND
JEREMIAH BECAUSE I'M THINKING OF
BLINDED SIDING L.J.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL CALL ME THE
OPPORTUNIST.
BECAUSE IF I SEE AN OPPORTUNITY
I'M GOING TO JUMP ON IT.
COMING BACK FROM THE
CHALLANGE, I'M JUST PICTURING
MYSELF GETTING MANI AND PEDI,
AND A NICE, COLD ONE
BOOM, I SNAPPED BACK INTO
REALITY, LIKE, OH, MAN, I'M
GOING TO BE PROBABLY SPEND HOURS
ON THE FIRE AND, YOU KNOW,
EATING A PLATE OF WHITE RICE
BUT, YOU KNOW.
ON A LIGHTER NOTE, IT'S KIND OF
NICE TO KNOW THAT MY BOY TONY
IS GOING TO KEEP AN EYE ON
SPENCER AND JEREMIAH AND JUST
MAKE SURE THEY DON'T JEOPARDIZE
OUR GAME PLAN.
>> THEY EARNED IT.
THEY KICKED OUR BUTT.
>> THEY DID, THEY REALLY DID.
>> DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I WOULD HAVE LOVED TO HAVE THIS
HIT.
I THINK WE ALL WOULD HAVE.
>> RIGHT.
>> AT THIS POINT, AT LEAST WE'RE
STILL HERE.
EVERYBODY IS DOWN BECAUSE WE
DIDN'T WIN THE REWARD BUT
PERSONALLY IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME
AS GREAT AS IT WOULD HAVE BEEN.
I'M STILL HERE IN THE GAME AND I
DO BELIEVE IN OUR CORE SIX AND I
THINK WEUL KNOW IT'S BEST IF WE
STICK AROUND-- TOGETHER RIGHT
NOW.
>> TONY'S GOT MAJOR ANXIETY
RIGHT NOW.
HE'S LIKE WHAT, DO YOU THINK OF
THE IDOL?
I THINK WOOS THAT?
SHOULD WE GET RID OF WOO SOON?
SHOULD WE GET RID OF WOO NOW?
SOME I'M JUST TRYING TO CALM HIM
DOWN.
>> RIGHT.
>> WE HAVE PLENTY OF VOTES.
>> WHAT'S HE WORRIED ABOUT,
YEAH?
>> THE FACT THAT TONY GOT A LOT
OF VOTES AT TRIBAL COUNCIL MADE
HIM REALLY FEEL LIKE, "THEY WANT
TO GET RID OF ME.
THEY WANT TO GET RID OF ME."
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I BUILT A STRONG BOND WITH TONY
BECAUSE MY LOYALTY IS THERE.
I PULLED THE IDOL OUT FOR HIM
AND I TRUST HE'LL DO THE RIGHT
THING.
THESE THREE PEOPLE HAVE TO GO
BEFORE ANYTHING-- TASH, SPENCER,
ASK JEREMIAH.
>> IF ANY OF THOSE THREE GO TO
THE END, THEY WIN.
>> ABSOLUTE.
>> IN THE BOTTOM LINE, WE NEED
TO PUT OUT TONY'S FIRE.
>> I'LL PUT OUT TONY'S FIRE.
>> OR ELSE WE'RE SCREWED.
>> TONY IS PANICKING BECAUSE HE
THINKS WOO MIGHT HAVE FOUND THE
IDOL.
I KNOW HOW TO GET TO TONY.
I CAN TELL TONY HE NEED TO
RELAX.
S DOWN WE HAVE TO STIX WITH SICK
WITH THE STIX.
>> I MADE A PLAN FOR FUTURE AND
IT RELIES ON PATIENCE AND SLONG
GO WITH THE PLAN WE COAL
EVERYTHING.
>> I THINK THE SIX OF US SHOULD
STAY STRONG BECAUSE THAT'S WANT
BEST SCENARIO FOR US THREE
SITTING HERE.
>> WELCOME.
>> JUST GRAB ONE?
>> VODKA AND RUM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU!
>> FOR ME, REWARD CHALLENGES ARE
A CHANCE TO BETTER MY POSITION
IN THE GAME.
RIGHT NOW, I DEFINITELY HAVE THE
ODDS STACKED AGAINST ME.
I'M NOT IN A POWERFUL POSITION.
AND I'M DOWN BUT I'M NOT OUT.
AND I'VE BEEN DOWN BEFORE.
AND I GOT BACK UP.
SO THERE'S NO REASON I CAN'T GET
IT BACK.
>> THIS IS QUITE AWESOME.
THIS IS WHAT WE GET.
I WAS HAPPY TO BE PAIRED UP WITH
JEREMIAH, WHO IS KIND OF LIKE MY
RIGHT-HAND MAN AT THIS POINT,
AND TONE, A GUY I WOULD LIKE TO
HEAR FROM AND SEE WHERE HIS HEAD
IS AT.
WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE IT WILL GIVE ME NEW LIFE
IN THE GAME.
>> OH, I FEEL GOOD.
>> WHAT'S UP, SPENCER.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK STRATEGY,
SEE WHERE YOUR HEAD IS AT?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GUYS THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO GET PICKED OFF ONE BY ONE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT'S NEVER THAT EASY, MAN.
>> IT DEPENDS WHERE YOUR HEAD IS
AT.
>> ARE YOU COMFORTABLE WHERE YOU
ARE RIGHT NOW?
>> NEVER COMFORTABLE, MY FRIEND.
SOMETHING IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU GIENS IT.
HANG IN THERE UNTIL THE TIME
COMES, AND WHEN THE TIME COMES
I'LL APPROACH YOU GUYS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
>> THE QUESTION SWILL THAT TIME
COME WHEN WE'RE HERE?
>> I THINK SO, I THINK SO, MAN.
>> I THINK BASICALLY WE'RE PAWNS
ON THE BOARD BUT YOU CAN USE US
IF YOU WANT.
>> TALKING TO JEREMIAH AND
SPENCER IS ALLOWING ME TO HAVE
ANOTHER BIG MOVE THAT WILL GET
ME TO THE TOP.
I JUST NEED THE VOTE WHEN IT'S
TIME TO TAKE L.J. OUT, AND THEN
I'LL GO BACK TO MY ALLIANCE BUT
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE DESPERATE.
WHEN PEOPLE ARE DESPERATE, YOU
DO THE THINKING FOR THEM.
WHATEVER I TELL THEM, THEY GO
WITH ME.
IF THEY GO AGAINST ME, THEY'RE
SEALING THEIR OWN FATE.
>> THAT FEELS GOOD RIGHT THERE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> THIS IS NICE, MAN.
>> I NEVER HAD ANYTHING LIKE
THIS BEFORE.
>> ARE YOU NOW, BUDDY.
>> YEAH, I'M IN IT.
>> WE COULD WORK SOMETHING OUT,
MAN, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I NEED TO KEEP YOU GUYS WHEN I'M
READY TO MAKE A BIG MOVE ON MY
TEAM.
I'M SURE SOMEBODY IS THINKING WE
HAVE TO GET RID OF TONY SOONER
OR LATER.
TONE'S' THREAT.
THEY'RE LOOK AT ME THAT WAY.
I NEED YOU GUYS TO HELP ME
ADVANCE.
THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL I CAN'T
GET RID OF TWO TWO.
I LIKE BIG MOVE.
>> TONY IS SAYING HE'S
GUARANTEEING HE HAS MY BACK.
HIS WHEELS ARE TURNING AND HE'S
PLAYING THE GAME.
RIGHT NOW I HAVE TO BELIEVE HIM
A LITTLE BIT.
STILL I HAVE MY DOUBTS.
HE MIGHT BE PLAYING US.
H>> IT JUST HAPPENED WE GOT HERE
BY CHANCE.
WE PICKED ROCKS PURPOSE WE WERE
ON THE SAME TEAM AND THAT'S HOW
THE GAME CHANGED.
THAT'S HOW THE GAME CHANGES ALL
THE TIME.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS ALL THAT.
>> RIGHT NOW I'LL BE HONEST.
I DON'T TRUST TONY THAT MUCH.
TONE SEPLAYING A LOT OF PEOPLE
RIGHT NOW.
HE'S JUGGLING A LOT OF BECAUSE,
AND I'M JUST ONE OF THEM.
HE DOESN'T THIS, BUT I HAVE AN
IDOL.
IF I FEEL UNEASY, I WON'T
HESITATE TO USE IT.
I'LL TELL TONY I TRUST HIM 100%
BECAUSE IF HE CAN TAKE ME A
LITTLE FURTHER DOWN THE ROAD, I
MIGHT FIND THE DETOUR THAT COULD
TAKE ME ALL THE WAY.
>> I ATE A LOT, BRO.
>> IT WAS LIKE A PICNIC.
JUST STARTED PIGGING OUT.
NO, IT WAS NICE.
>> IT'S DAY 25, AND I'M IN A
THREE-PERSON ALLIANCE UP AGAINST
A SIX-PERSON ALLIANCE.
IT DOESN'T TAKE A C.P.A., LIKE
MYSELF, TO DO THAT MATH.
SO I NEED TO CONVINCE SOMEONE TO
FLIP OR MAKE A BIG MOVE.
AND I THINK L.J. IS SMART ENOUGH
TO REALIZE THAT TONY IS NOT
GOING TO TAKE ANOTHER STRONG GUY
TO THE END.
WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO TALK?
>> I MEAN, I'M ALWAYS OPEN TO
LISTEN.
>> I HAVE A PROPOSITION FOR YOU.
IT'S REALLY GOOD, TOO.
>> TASHA WANTS TO TAKE ME ASIDE
AND HAVE A CONVERSATION.
I TOLD HER I WAS WILLING TO
LISTEN, BUT TONY IS A FLAMING
BALL OF ANXIETY RIGHT NOW, AND
IF I GO TAKE A WALK SOMEWHERE
WITH TASHA, THAT IS JUST MORE
FUEL TO THE FIRE.
EITHER WAY, THERE'S NO SITUATION
WHERE I FEEL LIKE SHE CAN
BENEFIT ME IN MY FUTURE GAME
PLAY.
BECAUSE I TRUST TONE PEP HE'S
THE REASON I'M STILL OUT HERE.
SO AS LONG AS WE STICK TO THE
PLAN WE HAVE INTACT, WE'LL BE
GOOD.
>> I INVITED L.J. TO RENDEZVOUS
WITH ME TO DISCUSS SOME
STRATEGY, AND HE STOOD ME UP.
IF L.J. WAS MAN ENOUGH TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE, HE CAN TAKE JEFF RARKS
SPENCER, JEREMIAH, AND I, AND
BLINDEDIDE TONY.
BUT IT'S CLEAR TONE SERUN THE
SHOW AROUND HERE AND EVERYONE IS
UNDER TONY'S THUMB.
SO UNLESS SOMETHING CHANGES, I'M
SCREWED.
>> TREE MAIL!
>> YES, ALL RIGHT.
>> FEELING GOOD AL ALREADY!
>> LET'S SEE HERE.
"PURPLE, BLURK YELLOW, AND RED.
LIKE SUNSETS, THE COLORS ARE
VIVID.
BLACK AND BLUES COULD BRUISE
YOUR EGO AND BEING VOTED OUT
COULD MAKE YOU LIVID."
>> OKAY...
>> THIS CHALLENGE TODAY IS HUGE.
I'M THINKING IN MY HEAD, L.J.'S
A CLEVER GUY.
IT'S GOING TO BE A MATTER OF WHO
THROWS THE FIRST PUNCH BETWEEN
THE BOTH OF US.
TIMING IS EVERYTHING, AND THIS
COULD BE MY TIME TO STRIKE.
IF L.J. DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY, HE
MIGHT BE THE NEXT ONE GOING
HOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST--
SPENCEY, TAKE IT BACK.
>> I'M LET YOU HOLD ON TO IT FOR
ME, JEFF.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
R 25 TAS DAYS OUT HERE, THE TOLL
THIS GAME HAS TAKEN ON YOUR
BODIES IS EVIDENT.
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO SEE WHAT
IT'S DONE TO YOUR MINDS.
TODAY'S CHALLENGE WILL TEST YOUR
MEMORY.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU A SERIES
OF CALEND COLORED TILES.
YOU'RE GOING TO REPEAT THEM BACK
TO ME.
GET IT RIGHT, YOU STAY ALIVE.
GET IT WRONG, YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
E,GUARANTEED A ONE IN EIGHT SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FIRST ROUND.
YELLOW.
BLUE.
RED.
GREEN.
THAT'S IT.
ALL RIGHT, GRAB YOUR FIRST
COLOR.
PLACE IT UP TOP.
AND DROP IT.
EVERYBODY SAYS YELLOW.
EVERYBODY'S CORRECT.
NEXT COLOR.
AND EVERYBODY DROP.
EVERYBODY SAYS BLUE EXCEPT
TRISH.
TRISH, THAT MEANS ARE YOU EITHER
ABOUT TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE OR
YOU ARE THE FIRST PERSON OUT.
DO YOU THINK IT IS?
>> I'M THE FIRST PERSON OUT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE THE FIRST
PERSON OUT.
>> SHOOT!
>> Jeff: BLUE WAS THE CORRECT
COLOR.
TRISH GOT IT WRONG.
HAVE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
NEXT COLOR, AND DROP IT.
EVERYBODY SAYS RED EXCEPT WOO.
GREEN IS NOT RIGHT.
THE CORRECT COLOR WAS RED.
WOO IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
>> IT'S HARD TONG, MAN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAST
COLOR.
EVERYBODY DROP.
EVERYBODY SAYS GREEN.
EVERYBODY'S RIGHT.
EVERYBODY STAYS ALIVE.
MOVING ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
RELEASE ALL YOUR COLORS, WE'LL
GO AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO, NEXT
ROUND.
RED.
GREEN.
PURPLE.
BLACK.
BLUE.
GREEN.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR FIRST COLOR.
EVERYBODY SAYS RED.
WE ARE OFF TO A GOOD START.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR NEXT COLOR.
EVERYBODY SAYS GREEN.
ONCE AGAIN, EVERYBODY RIGHT.
NEXT COLOR.
EVERYBODY SAYS PURPLE.
EVERYBODY RIGHT AGAIN.
NEXT COLOR.
EVERYBODY SAYS BLACK.
EVERYONE IS RIGHT.
NEXT COLOR.
BLUE IS RIGHT.
EVERYBODY GOT IT RIGHT.
NEXT COLOR.
SOMETHING YOU WOULD DO IN GRADE
SCHOOL CAN BE SO DIFFICULT AFTER
25 DAYS OF DEPRIVATION.
EVERYBODY DROP.
L.J., TASHA, AND TONY SAID
GREEN.
JEFRA, CAS, AND SPENCER SAID
YELLOW.
JEREMIAH SAID RED.
CORRECT ANSWER-- GREEN.
JEFRA'S WRONG, KASS GOT IT
WRONG.
SPENCER GOT IT WRONG, JEREMIAH'S
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE-- L.J.,
TASHA, AND TONY.
BIG IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
LAST COLOR.
EVERYBODY DROP.
WE HAVE THREE DIFFERENT RECALL
COLORS.
LK HAS RED.
TASHA HAS BLUE, TONY HAS YELLOW.
TONY, YOU'RE SHAKE YOUR HEAD.
>> Jeff: I THINK IT WAS WRONG.
IT WAS NOT YELLOW.
IT'S NOT YOURS.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
THAT LEAVES US WITH TWO.
HOW CONFIDENT ARE YOU L.J.?
>> PRETTY CONFIDENT.
>> Jeff: HOW ABOUT YOU TASHA?
>> SAME FOR ME.
>> Jeff: ONE OF YOU IS RIGHT.
ONE OF YOU IS WRONG.
CORRECT ANSWER IS... BLUE.
L.J.'S WRONG.
TASHA WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE )
TASHA, COME ON OVER.
>> WAY TO GO, TASHA.
>> Jeff: NO BETTER TIME THAN
RIGHT NOW TO HAVE IMMUNITY FOR
YOU.
>> I NEED IT.
>> Jeff: TASHA SAFE AT THE
VOTE TONIGHT.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
CONGRATS.
>> WHEN TASHA WON THE
IMMUNITY, IMMEDIATELY MY MIND
STARTED CRANKING.
ALL WE NEED TO DO IS SPLIT THE
VOTE 3-3, SO IF EVERYONE STICKS
TO THE PLAN ONE OF THEM IS GOING
HOME.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> CONGRATS.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> THAT WAS TOUGH, MAN.
I MISSED THE BLUE, MAN.
BY ONE I MISSED IT.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
THIS WAS A DO-OR-DIE CHALLENGE
FOR ME TODAY.
I KNEW I HAD A ONE-THIRD CHANCE
OF BEING VOTED OUT TONIGHT, SO
THIS PRETTY LITTLE THING AROUND
MY NECK SECURES THREE MORE DAYS
IN THIS GAME FOR ME.
SO, IN YOUR FACE, L.J.
>> HERE'S MY DEAL-- I THINK WE
SPLIT THE VOTE.
>> WHY-- WHY SPLIT?
BECAUSE OF THE IDOL?
>> YES, IF SOMEBODY FLIPS--
>> NOBODY IS GOING TO FLIP AT
THIS SAME OF THE GAME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I MEAN I HOPE NOT.
>> THAT'S THE BEST PLAY.
>> I ACTUALLY, FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN THIS GAME FEEL
COMFORTABLE.
WE HAVE A MAJORITY OF SIX.
SO SPENCER AND JEREMIAH ARE EASY
PICKINGS.
BUT TONY'S CONCERNED THAT WOO
MIGHT HAVE AN IDOL, AND MAYBE WE
SHOULD DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT,
WHICH IS SO STUPID.
I MEAN, WE MADE A PLAN THAT WE
ALL AGREED TO.
WE ALL DID OUR PINKY SWEAR, SO
WE JUST NEED TO STICK TO THE
PLAN.
>> WHO IS VOTING FOR WHO?
>> BOYS VOTE FOR JEREMIAH.
>> WE VOTE FOR SPENCER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HERE'S THE DEAL-- I'M NOT
GOING TO WAIT TO GET A PUNCH
THROWN AT ME BY L.J.
HE SAID HE WAS WILLING TO
BLINDSIDE WOO.
IT'S TRUE I SET HIM UP BUT I'M
GOING TO TRY TO PIN ALL THE
TROUBLE AT CAMP ON L.J., I HAVE
TO STRIKE NOW BEFORE HE GETS THE
IDEA OF DOING IT TO ME.
BUT FIRST I HAVE A LOT OF WORK
TO DO.
>> HE-- HE MIGHT BLINDSIDE
YOU, AND I DONT LIKE THAT.
IF HE'S WILLING TO BREAK HIS
PROMISE FOR YOU, HE'LL BE
WILLING TO BREAK HIS PROMISE FOR
ME.
>> THAT IS RIDICULOUS, THOUGH,
MAN.
I WAS 100% DOWN WITH THE SIX.
BUT, APPARENTLY, L.J., MR. CON
MAN, FOR SOME REASON WANTS TO
BLINDSIDE ME.
IF HE'S COMING TO TONY, MY
CLOSEST ALLY, AND SAYING WOO IS
GOING TO GO, WE MIGHT HAVE TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE BEFORE HE DOES.
>> HE'S WILLING TO BURN YOU.
SO IF YOU WANT TO-- YOU WANT TO
HAVE ANOTHER SHOCK FACE?
YEAH, I MEAN, I'M DOWN WITH
THAT.
I TRUST TONY THAT HE'S GOT MY
BACK.
SO IT'S GREAT TO HAVE HIM ON MY
SIDE.
AND IF ALL GOES WELL, MAN, IT'S
GOING TO BE ANOTHER HUGE NIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
TRUST ME, PLEASE, SPENCER.
>> TONY INITIALLY WANTED TO SAVE
ME AND JEREMIAH FOR A LATER
MOVE.
BUT, APPARENTLY, L.J. IS
PLOTTING TO GET OUT WOO.
SO TONY'S READY TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE NOW.
>> I'M DEFINITELY STOKED.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE CHRISTMAS
MORNING EYE WOKE UP EXPECTING TO
SEE NOTHING BUT ASHES AND COAL
UNDER THE TREE, AND THERE'S THIS
PRESENT OF "LET'S VOTE OUT L.J."
IT'S KIND OF TOO GOOD TO BE
TRUE.
THIS COULD BE A BIG LIE SO THAT
I DON'T PLAY MY IMMUNITY IDOL
TONIGHT.
STILL, I'M GOING TO TAKE
ANYTHING I CAN GET RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE IF I CAN JUST GET A
LITTLE BIT FURTHER DOWN THE
ROAD, HAVE A FEW VOTES GO MY
WAY, IT'S A WHOLE NEW GAME FOR
ME.
SO THINGS ARE HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW.
TONY'S PROBABLY TARGETING L.J.
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE SOLID--
>> I'M SOLID WITH YOU.
AND WE'LL BE SOLWID THEM.
I CAME INTO THIS TRIBE WITH
NOTHING.
>> SO WE JUST GOTTA BE CAREFUL
BECAUSE HE'S A SMART GUY.
>> HE'S VERY DANGEROUS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
HE'S VERY DANGEROUS.
>> RIGHT NOW WE CAN JUST LET
THEM KILL EACH OTHER AND WE'RE
GOOD.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> L.J. WAS CONCERNED THAT YOU
WERE REALLY WORRIED ABOUT WOO.
>> I WASN'T CONCERNED.
HE WAS CONCERNED.
HE WANTED TO VOTE HIM OUT, AND
MY FACE TURNED COLORS BECAUSE IT
WAS LIKE WE HAD AN AGREEMENT.
>> HE TOLD ME YOU WANTED TO VOTE
HIM OUT.
>> I KNOW YOU LIKE L.J., BUT I
THINK HE'S SNEAKY, TRISH, MAN.
>> HE TOLD ME THAT YOU THOUGHT
WOO WAS A THREAT AND THAT YOU
WERE PANICKING AND THAT YOU
WANTED TO THROW WOO OUT BUT THAT
HE DIDN'T THINK THAT WAS A GOOD
IDEA.
>> MOARKS MAN, HE'S LYING TO
YOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK L.J. WANTS, TO
COME IN FOURTH PLACE?
IT'S ME, IT'S YOU AND IT'S WOO.
IT'S US THREE AGAINST JEFRA AND
L.J.
YOU DON'T THINK HE'S THINKING
ABOUT THAT?
HE'S ALREADY PLANNING AHEAD,
TRISH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU PROPOSING?
>> I'M NOT PROPOSING ANYTHING
RIGHT NOW.
>> TONY IS GET REALLY, REALLY
PARANOID.
HE TOLD ME TODAY AT THE WELL
THAT L.J. IS TRYING TO BREAK THE
SIX BUT L.J. TOLD ME A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT STORY.
HE SAID, "OH, MY GOD, TONY IS
TOTALLY FREAK OUT.
HE WANTS WOO GONE."
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO BELIEVE
NOW.
>> SAY ME, YOU, WOO, THROW
L.J.'S NAME DOWN, RIGHT, AND
THEN WE TELL TASH, SPENCER, AND
JEREMIAH TO THROW L.J.'S NAME
DOWN--
>> I'M STILL THINKING WE SHOULD
ALL KEEP OUR PROMISE TO THE
FINAL SIX.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT?
>> I WOULD THINK SO, BUT NOW I
DON'T TRUST L.J.
>> I JUST-- WHY DO YOU THINK HE
TOLD ME YESTERDAY THAT YOU
WANTED WOO OFF, AND IT WAS HIM
THAT--
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S GOING TO TRY SOMETHING
SNEAKY, MAN.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> OH, MAN, TRISH, YOU DON'T SEE
IT, MAN.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY POSSIBLE L.J.
IS UP TO SOMETHING.
I THINK L.J. IS UP TO A LOT
BECAUSE HE WANTS TO WIN BUT TONY
HAS ALSO PLAYED ME AND I AM
GULLIBLE BUT I'M NOT STUPID SO
THERE'S NO WAY I'M BREAKING UP
THE SIX.
>> EVERYONE'S GOOD, RIGHT?
YOU'RE SURE?
>> I THINK SO WHEN TONY HAD HIS
NAME WRITTEN DOWN FOUR TIMES--
>> HE WAS PISSED.
AND I SAID, "JUST TAKE A CHILL
PILL.
OF.
>> NOBODY NEEDS TO MEAS THIS UP
RIGHT NOW.
I LOVE A GOOD BLINDSIDE, BUT
IT'S TOO SOON.
NO ONE WANTS TO MAKE A BIG MOVE
RIGHT NOW.
YOU'D BE STUPID, AND I THINK
TONY KNOWS THAT.
ALL SIX OF US ARE IN A GREAT
POSITION AS LONG AS WE STICK
WITH OUR ALLIANCE.
>> DO YOU THINK HE'S GOING TO GO
THROUGH WITH IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M 50-50 ON HIM.
>> RIGHT NOW, I HAVE A HUGE PLAN
IN PLAY BUT TRISH IS TELLING ME
LET'S KEEP THE SIX STRONG SO IF
I GET RID OF L.J. THERE ARE
GOING TO BE A LOT OF HARD
FEELINGS.
TRISH HAS BEEN WITH ME SINCE DAY
ONE.
SHE IS MY CLOSEST ALLY BUT IF I
DO THIS SHE COULD TURN HER BACK
ON ME AND THAT THE WHOLE THING
WOULD BLOW UP IN MY FACE.
IF THAT'S THE CASE, I HAVE TO
STICK WITH MY ALLIANCE.
IN LIFE, AS IN "SURVIVOR" YOU
NEED TO KNOW WHEN TO KISS ASS OR
KISS ASS, AND RIGHT NOW I MIGHT
HAVE TO KISS ASS, AND GET RID OF
SPENCER OR JEREMIAH.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
SARAH, AND MORGAN, VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, JEREMIAH, UNLESS SOMETHING
DRASTIC HAS CHANGED, IT WOULD
SEEM THAT YOU, TASHA, AND SPERNS
WOULD ALL STILL BE IN TROUBLE
WITH THE OTHER SIX STILL TIGHT.
>> YEAH, THAT'S A STRONGS SIX
RIGHT THERE.
YOU KNOW, ME AND SPENCER IS KIND
OF LOOKING AT EACH OTHER LIKE,
OH, MAN, THIS AIN'T GOOD.
>> Jeff: KASS, YOU'RE A BIG
REASON WE NOW HAVE THIS
DIVISION.
IS THERE ANY EMPATHY FROM YOU
TOWARDS THESE THREE THAT YOU
USED TO BE A PART OF?
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S THE GAME,
JEFF, AND FROM HEREON OUT PEOPLE
MIGHT START MAKING MOVES LIKE
WHAT I MADE.
YOU CAN'T PLAY THIS GAME AND NOT
GET A LITTLE DIRT. TONY, KASS
SAYS YOU CAN'T PLAY THIS GAME
WITHOUT GETTING A LITTLE DIRTY.
>> YEAH, THAT'S TRUE, JEFF.
IT'S JUST A BUNCH OF CONFUSION
OUT HERE BUT DON'T KNOW WHO IS
SAYING WHAT, WHO IS TELLING THE
TRUTH.
WHEN WE COME TO THIS GAME WE'RE
ACCEPTING FACT THAT WE'RE GOING
TO BE DECEIVED, THAT WE'RE GOING
TO GET STABBED IN THE BACK, AND
THAT'S WHY I BROUGHT MY BAG OF
TRICKS WITH ME TODAY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S IN THE BAG OF
TRICKS.
>> WE'LL PROBABLY FIND OUT
TONIGHT BUT IT'S SOMETHING TO
MAKE ME FEEL MORE COMFORT HERE
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: TASHA, THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT TO HEAR.
IF THERE'S A TIGHT SIX, WHY
WOULD TONY SAY I BROUGHT MY BAG
OF TRICKS AND WE'LL PROBABLY
FIND OUT TONIGHT?
>> THAT'S WHY I'M GLADE HAVE
THIS LOVELY NECKLACE AROUND MY
NECK.
ALLIANCES APPEAR REALLY TIGHT,
BUT THE LONGER YOU CAN STAY IN
IT, THE MORE YOU MIGHT SEE
FRACTURES IN TIGHT ALLIANCES.
>> Jeff: L.J., TASHA JUST USED
AIR QUOTES TO DESCRIBE YOUR
ALLIANCE.
>> I THINK THAT SHE'S JUST
GETTING A REALITY CHECK AND IS
HOPEFUL THAT THERE IS SOME
SORT OF CRACK IN OUR ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: WERE YOU APPROACHED
TODAY BY SPENCER OR TAWSH OR
JEREMIAH TO LOOK FOR THAT CRACK
JIEFS VAGUELY APPROACHED.
BUT I TOOK A STEP BACK AND
REALIZED THERE'S NO TREEN CAUSE
ANXIETY MOONGZ THE GROUP.
I MEAN, WE'RE PRETTY WATER
TIGHT.
>> Jeff: IN YOUR LINE OF WORK,
L.J., HOW BIG IS LOYALTY?
>> IT'S HUGE.
PUT IT'S A VERY DIFFICULT THING
TO FIND.
...
>> Jeff: SO DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE A GOOD GAUGE OF IT?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I THINK I HAVE
A VERY SHARP EYE.
I'M VERY HONED IN TO THINGS THAT
CAN BE DISLOYAL AND SO I THINK I
HAVE A PRETTY GOOD GAUGE.
>> Jeff: TONY, LINE OF WORK,
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> CONSTRUCTION.
>> Jeff: LOYALTY PLAY A PART
IN THE CONSTRUCTION BUSINESS?
>> YES, YOU'LL SEE IT OVER AND
OVER, JEFF.
YOU TURN YOUR EYE, ONE OF YOUR
TOOLS IS MISSING.
TRUST IS A VERY, VERY DIFFICULT
THING, JEFF, ESPECIALLY IN
"SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: KASS, LOYALTY, COME
INTO PLAY FOR YOU?
>> AT HOME, YES.
BUT I TRIED TO CHECK MY LIFE AT
THE DOOR WHEN I CAME ON HERE.
YOU HAVE TO BE 100% SELFISH IF
YOU'RE GOING TO GET FIRE IN THIS
GAME.
IT'S "SURVIVOR, NOT LIFE BUT
IT'S HARD TO RECONCILE THAT.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF THE GAME,
YOU'RE CONSTANTLY FIGHTING WITH
WHETHER YOU'RE A PLAYER OR
PERSON AND CAN YOU BE BOTH OF
THESE?
>> Jeff: WOO, IF LOYALTY IS
VERY IMPORTANT, WHEN DO YOU GET
TO THE POINT WHERE YOU SAY I
HAVE SOME THREAT TO MY AEXPLIENS
I I NEED TO GET RID OF THEM?
>> AT THIS POINT, JEFF, EVERYONE
IS GOING TO BE PRONE AND
SUSCEPTIBLE, A LITTLE PARANOIA.
OUR SIX IS STILL STRONG SO MIGHT
AS WELL GO WITH THE FLOW, START
TAKING OUT THE BOTTOM THREE, BUT
WE'RE GOING TO COME TO THAT TIME
WHERE WE'RE GOG HAVE TO NAIK
MOVES.
>> Jeff: SPENCER, DO YOU LOOK
THAT SIX AND THINK I
I KNOW WHO IS ON THE BOTTOM? I
DON'T KNOW WHO IS ON THE BOTTOM.
I DON'T.
BUT I DO KNOW ONE IS ON THE
BOTTOM BUT IF YOU'RE ONE BEING
TOLD WE'RE A TIGHT SIX, THERE
ARE NO DIVISIONS IN THE SIX,
MAYBE YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
AND IT IS TIME PEOPLE START
THINKING ABOUT HOW CAN I PUT
MYSELF IN A POSITION TO WIN?
>> Jeff: TRISH, IS THERE ANY
PART OF YOU THINKING, SOME
SOMEBODY'S ON THE BOTTOM, THIS
IS THE TIME TO MAKE A MOVE?
>> WELL THINK OF, I THINK THIS
"BRADY BUNCH" IS GOING TO BECOME
VERY DISFUNCTIONAL VERY QUICKLY.
I THINK I GOT VERY COMFORTABLE
THINKING WE'RE SIX AND THEY'RE
THREE AND THEN YOU START
THINKING IT DOESN'T END AT THIS.
IT REALLY BEGINS AT THIS BECAUSE
SOMETHING HAS TO BREAK AND
THAT'S WHAT I ANTICIPATE IS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: IT WILL HAPPEN.
THE QUESTION IS WHEN?
IT COULD HAPPEN TONIGHT.
IF IT DID, THAT WOULD BE
SOMETHING I WOULD BE COMPLETELY
UNAWARE OF.
BUT EVERY TIME I COME TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THIS PLACE GOES CRAZY.
BUT THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT SO FUN
AND THAT'S WHAT MAKES YOUR
STOMACH SICK AT THE SAME TIME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
WOO, YOU'RE UP.
>> FINGERS CROSSED.
HERE'S TO ANOTHER BLINDSIDE.
.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, L.J.
L.J.
LK.
THAT'S THREE VOTES L.J.
JEREMIAH.
THREE VOTES JEREMIAH, THREE
VOTES L.J.
SPENCER.
ONE VOTE SPENCER.
L.J.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES L.J.
THREE VOTES JEREMIAH.
ONE VOTE SPENCER, ONE VOTE LEFT.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY, L.J.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> WELL PLAYED.
IS THERE L.J., THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME TO GO.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> DID YOU FLIP?
WOW.
>> Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT'S VOTE
AND REACTIONS TO IT IS PROOF
ONCE AGAIN, "SURVIVOR" IS AN
INDIVIDUAL GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> TODAY I'M ON A MISSION.
>> Jeff: TONY WILL STOP AT
NOTHING TO STAY AHEAD OF THE
GAME.
>> I'M GOING TO TRY TO GET UP
THERE.
>> Jeff: WHILE WOO'S MISSION
FOR FOOD GOES HORRIBLY WRONG.
>> YEAH!
>> COME ON DOWN, BROTHER!
>> SO I WAS CLEARLY BLINDSIDED.
IT'S VERY HARD TO FIND THE
BALANCE BETWEEN PATIENCE AND
BEING ASSERTIVE, BECAUSE IF
YOU MOVE TOO SOON, YOU CAN BITE
YOURSELF IN THE BUTT.
BUT IF YOU WAIT TOO LONG, YOU
CAN SEE YOURSELF LOOKING INTO A
LENS SAYING WHERE DID I GO
WRONG?