translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
All clashed
around the idols,
and it was Spencer
who found one.
He's a simple idol, but
I potentially bought some time.
But the idol
with different powers
remained to be discovered.
It's protection
I would love to have.
I have to find this idol.
Moreover,
two alliances clashed.
We have a majority of six.
Tasha, Spencer and Jeremiah
are easy targets.
But at the last reward,
Tony saw an opportunity
to use the minority alliance
to their advantage.
LJ is shady.
I'll just need them
when it's time to eliminate LJ.
Then I will join my alliance.
- Let them kill each other.
- Yeah.
And everything will go just fine.
And at the council,
he got what he wanted.
Ninth Person Eliminated
- LJ.
He took LJ and his alliance by surprise .
LJ, the tribe has spoken.
There are eight left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
- It was interesting.
- I love this game.
Who switched sides?
Just Woo?
- Or Woo and Tony?
- Woo and me.
- And Tony?
- Yeah.
They offered us
to be five against LJ.
Why?
- I have many.
- Alright, let's talk about it.
I couldn't tell you,
or Trish, or Kass,
because you like LJ,
you wouldn't have understood my reasons.
Tony completely mystified LJ.
First, I said to myself:
"I would have liked to know".
But I immediately understood
why he hadn't told me anything.
He feared
the plan would fall through.
So I wasn't mad.
I still trust Tony,
and Tony still trusts me.
Is it a one-time alliance?
So I'm not
down the covenant?
It does not exist.
Every time we promise
a six-man final,
it does not work.
It's true.
I like to try to anticipate
the actions of others.
Tony is not so predictable.
He likes to do big hits,
and I'm not complaining about it,
because it benefited me,
but he could
start again later,
and I can't
always count on him.
Could we tell Woo
we were eliminating Cliff? Nope!
Sometimes you can't
say everything to some,
because it creates chaos.
The sooner we can act against Tony,
the better.
I'm very united
with Jeremiah and Tasha.
Now it's a matter of knowing,
among those who are lagging behind,
who we can board
to make a hit.
My warning flag is up,
because I eliminated
LJ by surprise.
I'm in trouble
I have to
do something to get out of it.
Most people, myself included,
we go the water way,
because it's a bit far from the camp,
away from the ears,
and this is where we talk about strategy.
So I started to work
to a small cabin
near the well.
The well is here.
There is a tree there.
I put bushes,
shrubs, branches,
so that I could hide there
less than two meters away.
This is where I will wait,
sitting in my spy hut.
Sorry, but I don't want
to be fooled by Tony,
because honestly, I think
he's playing us, Trish.
I would like to know
how you see our situation.
Is there only one covenant?
I believe him. It's us five...
I think the alliance
remains strong without LJ.
OK.
Because then, we continue
to eliminate the three, huh?
But Tony
took the wrong career.
He deserves an Oscar.
I say.
We have to be careful.
During my watch,
I overheard Jefra and Trish talking.
Trish said Tony deserved
an Oscar for his acting skills.
Eliminate LJ, okay,
but that's his way of doing it
Which means
I don't trust Tony.
He lied to me,
and he wants us to be allies?
At this point,
I trust Trish.
I trust Woo.
I trust Kass.
And that's all.
I no longer trust Jefra
because she no longer trusts me,
and if she doesn't trust me,
I won't trust her.
So for now,
I'm in trouble.
Survivor Season 28 Episode 10
Sitting in My Spy Shack
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
- Yes.
- We are.
Today you will be divided
into two teams of four.
On my signal, you will race
to collect oars.
When you have them all,
two team members will use it
to solve a word puzzle.
Want to know what's at stake?
The four winners will leave from here
for a place of the most
- the Kalau caves,
where you will enjoy a barbecue.
Chicken.
- Sides.
- Oh my God.
- Potato salad.
Chocolate chip cookies.
Is it worth it?
Absolutely.
We will create the teams
and we will start. Let's go!
We have our two teams.
Tasha, Jephra, Spencer and Jeremiah.
Here we go, for the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Mounted! Come on, Jeremiah!
Jefra struggles from the start,
she didn't board fast enough,
which slows down the purple quartet.
The Oranges go
in all directions.
These large boats are not
easy to maneuver.
Stay in the same place!
Go on! To the right!
It's teamwork.
You have to go all the way
before they can come back
and pick up the oars.
Let's not panic.
Tasha effectively leads her team.
Tasha, Jefra, Spencer
and Jeremiah are in the lead,
they approach
their first box of oars.
There are eight oars in all,
four boxes.
You have it!
Tasha unties the oars
for her team.
Woo will do it for his team.
There are two oars per box.
When you have them,
move on to the next box.
- You got them?
- Yes.
Tasha has the first oar.
I got it.
Woo has the first oar
for his team.
Tony helps Woo now.
Tasha does this alone.
Tony and Woo take the lead.
Go on!
Tasha finally has her second oar.
The Oranges picked up the pace.
Woo attacks
the second box of oars.
The Violets are on their way
to their second box.
- Sorry, Jefra, how are you?
- How are you.
No problem, keep going.
Woo and Tony have the second oars
for the Oranges.
They stay ahead.
Jeremiah always unties those knots.
Tony has lost an oar,
he has to go back!
It's going to cost
his team a lot of time.
You need these oars
to complete!
He must go up.
Carry on, carry on!
No, you have to get back on board!
Spencer and Jeremiah
have the second oars.
Tony, back on board.
Equality again.
All the way to the right!
Tony has the second oar.
The Oranges continue.
Let's go!
Tasha and Jefra have the second oar,
they continue.
It's always neck and neck.
There is one box left.
Two more oars.
To be!
You and is?
Tony and Woo are on the
last two Oranges trains.
The Violets have passed the box.
U-turn, U-turn!
Huge waste of time.
They must come back.
Tony is on the last
orange team train,
and he has it.
Come back, and attack the puzzle!
Spencer and Tasha
need to straighten things out.
Full left!
Ready?
The Violets have the second oar,
they are in on it again!
Start bringing the oars up.
Nice teamwork from the Oranges
to bring all the oars quickly...
- Oars, oars!
- ...on the platform.
Take the last one, Spencer.
Detach them all,
then attack the puzzle.
OK, here we go.
The Oranges have all the oars.
The Violets have all the oars.
Attack the puzzle!
Place them all and watch them!
Place them and watch them!
It's Woo and Kass for the Oranges.
Tasha and Spencer for the Violets.
Nothing. Put an N! NO, NO!
There is a N?
It's a three-word sentence.
For the first,
a barbecue afternoon.
The final. The final.
Yes go ahead!
- Final?
- They have "final".
- An idea? Give it a shot!
- Like that.
Spencer and Tasha peep next door.
- Advice?
- Wrestle. Wrestle.
They try to guess this sentence.
What is the link with the reward?
"It's worth fighting for."
Woo and Kass change their oars,
they have a completely different idea.
They change everything.
Put that at the end!
We have to think for ourselves.
"It's worth playing."
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Spencer and Tasha are watching.
They think they have found it.
It could be
a sprint to the finish.
Are you right?
Yes, that's it, that's it!
No that's not it.
But if.
A letter is missing!
It's worth playing!
And they mark,
"it's worth playing"!
Tasha, Jefra, Jeremiah
and Spencer win the reward!
Sorry to bump your head.
Shit.
That's what I was saying,
a letter was missing.
huge win, great reward.
Grab your things, go ahead,
and enjoy!
I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
We lost the race.
The first thing I say to myself,
we're in trouble.
Tony is in trouble too,
but here, we all have them.
Jefra, who no longer believes in me,
and no longer believes
that she belongs to an alliance.
It is a problem. It's going to go wrong.
Home, sweet home.
A defeat has never
made me so bitter,
but we must
recognize their merit.
The worst is
Tash, Jeremiah and Spencer.
Yes, they will absorb... attract...
They will talk to Jefra.
I'm tired of losing.
But to make a million,
I have to stick with these five:
- I'm going to get some water.
- You need help?
No, I'm going alone.
From my point of view,
Tony felt threatened
and got rid of LJ.
It doesn't hurt me
that someone makes a move.
Tony is annoying,
but my philosophy,
it is to keep the annoying ones
and eliminate the dangerous ones.
If Spencer loses immunity,
he has to leave.
Me, him, Jefra, Trish and you.
We didn't promise you anything,
but we promised each other,
and we can include you
in the promise,
because we didn't break any promises
to LJ.
Lord, are we strategizing?
You have to, Trish.
Do you know how
dangerous these rewards are?
Jefra is alone, what do you think?
I don't know,
but I trust
in these lemons and these papayas
that I have just found.
If anyone wants to
come see it with me,
I'll be back to strategize
all day.
I tell Trish I'm
trying to talk strategy,
to act, to enlighten
him on what is happening.
On the importance of this day.
This could be
the beginning of our end.
And she asks where are
the lemons and papayas!
Wanna help me, Woo?
Because you know how to climb,
you may have to climb.
OK.
So Tony has to strategize alone,
as usual.
I just need
a few minutes alone.
I'll go get the idol.
Lemons and papayas!
It must be a joke.
Regarding the idol
of the banks of the river,
it's very possible that
Spencer, Tash or Jeremiah have it.
But at the merger, we were told:
"near your camp is hidden
an idol with special powers".
That's all I know.
Let me find this idol,
and I'll be Super Tony.
Tony won't be in trouble anymore.
Where the hell is she?
You see that?
Oh my God, look at them!
Looks like Morgan's breasts.
Don't go any further, just shake.
- It's coming.
- Lemons and papayas!
I shake this papaya tree,
I shake, I shake, boom!
And I harvest at least
seven huge papayas.
How are you?
The branch in my right hand
was dead,
I didn't realize it.
I tried to play it like
Sylvester Stallone in Cliffhanger.
I swing my left hand,
but immediately, crack!, and...
- Ah, my ass!
- Something broken?
- Whoa, how are you?
- Yes, I am fine.
- Is it normal that...?
- It's like a cramp.
Oh no, I hope
you didn't break your tailbone.
Spencer, Jeremiah,
Jefra and Tasha, wow!
They live
an exceptional reward.
that's all
I didn't want to happen."
No, don't get up!
My ass! Ouch, my ass!
But I was very lucky
to get away with it.
We got fresh papayas
and lemons,
so, you know... I'm thrilled.
I'm ready to bust my ass
every day for papayas.
- It's splendid.
- That's crazy.
We don't experience this every day.
I had never been
in a cave.
Pay attention.
- It slips.
- Everything is fine.
Wow, that's too good.
The reward was really,
really nice.
The cave was huge,
it was exceptional.
There is no other word.
It's awesome!
Here is your meal.
- Lord, look at this!
- Thanks.
I'll leave you, I'll be back soon.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks for the visit.
Although the cave was beautiful,
the table full of food
was even more so.
It was a barbecue
like at home.
Tell me everything.
How many ribs for you?
- Of them.
- Do you want two?
- Okay, let's say three.
- Yeah, that looks good.
- How's the tea?
- It is good.
I was at the reward,
with nothing to distract me.
With my main allies,
Jeremiah and Tasha,
and Jefra, who we have to recruit.
It was perfect, because I need
that Jefra is comfortable with
this group of four.
How are you feeling, Jefra?
I'm a bit lost at this point.
because there was a big blow,
and I didn't know,
neither Trish nor Kass.
So good, whatever,
but I wonder
about my place in the alliance.
I'm wondering.
- Or if you have a place.
- Exactly.
No one has an interest in keeping Tony.
- We agree?
- OK.
- Yes.
- I agree.
Tony must be the first.
Tony first, clearly.
Jefra, how would you like
to work with us?
I need another rib
to think about it.
Eat as much as you want!
- Anyone want some?
- Excuse me.
I have something else for you.
- Oh my God.
- My God.
Oh my God.
That's what I think?
- I know what it is.
- Oh, Lord.
Jefra knows what it is.
Even before having
the letter of my loved ones in hand,
I was shaking and crying,
that's exactly what I needed.
My mother's words
touched me so deeply...
Even if we
really don't want to crack,
even if we
really don't want to cry,
sometimes we have no choice.
I can't even look
at my mother's letter.
"Don't let
your kind heart be your downfall,
don't be afraid to lie,
even if you're not like that."
It's probably a sign for me.
I should probably
switch sides at this point.
I firmly believe
that there is a reason for everything.
I don't doubt it for a moment,
I won the award because
I needed to hear
what my mother had to say to me.
- Final square?
- Final square.
- Let's all shake hands.
Final square, baby.
- You already shook my hand, buddy.
- I say.
Everyone shakes hands.
You shook my hand before.
I'll remind you this time.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
You know what that means, Tasha.
First of all...
I recover it.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will stand
on a narrow rail,
while keeping a ball
balanced on a platform.
At regular intervals,
you will descend
to a narrower part.
Your hands will descend
along the pole,
making it more difficult to balance.
If you fall off the rail
or drop the ball,
you are eliminated from the test.
The last person standing
wins immunity,
ensures a one in seven chance
of winning this game.
The losers, tribal council,
where someone will be eliminated.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Alright, everybody
in starting position.
Place your balls
on your platforms.
Balance them and hold them
waiting for my signal.
Let's go.
Three, two, one.
Let go.
This test is launched,
and from the first second,
the wind picks up, right at the right time.
It stirs many balls.
Kass struggles to keep
his ball on his platform.
And suddenly,
Jefra is eliminated from the event.
His ball falls.
Jefra is the first eliminated.
Tony struggles to hold on.
Trish drops her ball,
she is eliminated.
Tony drops his ball,
he is eliminated.
When it happens, it happens quickly.
Suddenly, Kass is eliminated.
There are
only four people left.
Three minutes elapsed
in this first round.
This first round
will last ten minutes.
Then we will increase the difficulty.
Only ten seconds left
in this round.
I will count.
Stay focused, it's not over.
Five, four, three, two, one.
You are safe.
Go to the next level.
Lower your hands down
a notch on the pole.
And replace your balls.
Alright, here we go. I will count.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Let go.
Everyone is now
in round two.
It will last ten minutes.
Tash has some problems, right off the bat.
But it stabilizes quickly.
Jeremiah fails
to recover his ball, he is eliminated.
He won't know
what it's like to be immune.
All three
have already won immunity.
All three know
this feeling of protection.
All three would like
to know him again.
Only ten seconds left
in this round.
Here comes another gust of wind.
Hold on,
don't let go now.
Five, four, three, two, one.
You are safe.
Good work.
Now go to the
narrowest part of the rail.
This is the
most difficult part of the test.
Now get your hands down
at the bottom of the pole.
Everyone looks good.
Put your balls back
on the platform, I'll count down.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This test resumes.
The rail is narrower.
And you have
a longer pole to maintain.
This makes balancing
more difficult.
It will take more control
to perform a recovery.
Woo is in control,
but he can't hold on.
Woo falls,
and there are only two left.
Once again, Tasha and Spencer.
We have seen this clash before.
Spencer had won.
There is no longer a time limit.
We will continue until
one of you falls.
Nice recovery from Tasha.
There you go, pick yourself up and you'll be fine.
There's a little wind again.
Nice recovery from Spencer,
but he does not succeed,
Spencer is eliminated.
Tasha wins individual immunity!
She secures a place
in the last seven!
Tasha, come here.
Tasha, once again,
safe at tonight's council.
As for you,
after 28 very difficult days,
someone's dream
to finish this game
and earning a million,
will end.
Pack your things,
head back to camp,
See you tonight at council.
Congratulation.
Thanks, Jeff.
I don't feel
safe with Tony.
The rest of the alliance
believes everything he says.
Like he was Jesus
or something.
At the moment, I have more confidence
in Tasha, Jeremiah and Spencer.
And this could be my chance
to knock Tony out now,
rather than having
to do it later.
- Well done, Tash.
- Tash, one more time.
- You did it!
- Nice job, Tasha.
Yeah, no, no.
- It was good.
- This third level...
- I wasn't going to last long.
- Neither do I.
- It wasn't for me.
- Nope.
For now the plan is that
Spencer, Jeremiah, me and Jefra
eliminate Tony by surprise.
But the problem,
is that it could
be 4 against 4.
We might have to vote again,
then pull the rocks.
But we think
the person
the most important one to eliminate
at this point is Tony.
Once again,
no collar for Tony.
So today,
I'm not chopping wood,
I don't make a fire,
I don't boil water.
I have a mission.
I need an idol.
In other Survivor seasons,
it's still an iconic location.
There is a well-worn tree
behind our mailbox.
I had looked there the first time,
I will look again.
I'm looking for the special idol,
and you know what?
I will find her.
Please.
Let her be there.
You are really upset.
I see it on your face.
I know you and Tony
are very close, but...
I don't feel safe
in our alliance.
Back at camp, I notice
that there is a problem with Jefra.
She does not hide her feelings,
and she was almost
on the verge of tears.
She thinks she's at the bottom of the wedding ring.
She no longer trusts Tony.
He acts like he's got it
both ways.
but I'm sick
of his falsity.
I'm sick
of his lies about LJ.
It's like...
He gets on my nerves.
So I'm going to the freak tree.
There is nothing.
"Let's follow the path,
in case something goes out
of the lot".
Looks like a rocket.
I come to a tree,
it looks like a rocket.
It had huge roots,
I had never seen anything like it.
"I have to search here".
Please.
I start digging, scratching.
Oh, damn it.
And I feel something.
So I grab a stick,
and I dig, I dig, I dig.
Go on.
There is something.
"Please
let it be that"!
Oh my God!
I almost fainted,
I was so happy.
Then I opened it,
and it's the special idol.
My God!
I love you so much.
This special idol
is priceless.
"This immunity idol
will protect you
from elimination to tribal council.
Unlike
other immunity idols,
it can be played
after the votes have been read."
Can we use
it after seeing the votes?
Everyone will do...
"This idol only protects
the person who finds it,
you can't give it
to someone else."
I'll hide it now,
then I'll go wash up.
I have to go.
I have to go wash up.
Do you realize
its power?
I will show you its power!
In this game, every time
you eliminate
someone who annoys you,
it plays against you.
But I can't take it anymore.
Like everyone.
That's why you have to keep it.
So, here's the thing.
We can't eliminate him tonight.
If we eliminate him tonight,
we empower all three.
We can't do that,
because we won't beat them in the end.
We have a much better chance
of beating Tony and Woo in the final.
Tony, we need to be able
to trust you.
We need to be able
- Because otherwise...
- Don't insult me, Trish.
- I know, I'm just saying...
- Don't insult me.
Everyone is freaking out
that you're playing double agent.
Who is that?
Everybody.
- The double agent stunt.
- It's... It's...
- I'm wondering.
- It makes people paranoid.
I understand, Trish.
But if you know who I am,
what kind of man I am,
and that I gave you my word...
One two three four five.
All three will leave.
I guarantee it.
I swear on my baby,
I swear on my father,
I swear it on my mother,
I swear it on everyone.
I cast doubts
on Tony's integrity,
and he admitted that playing
the double agent wouldn't work.
And Jefra needed to see me
ask her for an explanation.
That's why I did this.
But I believe her to be loyal,
she will not change sides.
I think Spencer has the idol.
- Yeah.
- I can read people.
Wow, what do you think?
If Spencer has an idol...
So we have it in the bone.
Tasha is safe tonight,
so eliminating Spencer
seems obvious.
Considering
he's good with the jury,
and that he is very capable
of winning immunity trials.
Jeremiah, on the other hand,
is an athlete,
which also jeopardizes our chances.
But there is one thing
we are not sure about.
And that's who has an idol.
Jeremiah, can
I talk to you for a second?
I know I made a commitment
to you the other day,
- but I will not vote with you.
- OK.
I hope you understand,
it's in my interest.
- Nothing personal.
- Very well.
I saw Jefra in the water
with all his wedding ring,
so everyone except me,
spencer and tasha,
and I knew
something was up.
- OK.
- Yeah.
- Its good.
- Sorry.
I had put a little trust
in her, she shook my hand,
she promised and everything,
but I guess
the pressure took over.
Everyone knows
what to expect now.
Can I tell you something
that I haven't told anyone?
- Are we okay?
- Yeah.
I am a model.
No wonder you're so hot!
Jeremiah realized
there was a real chance
let one of us
go tonight.
He therefore decided to spill the beans
and reveal that he is a model.
If you google my name,
Jeremiah Wood,
add "mannequin" at the end,
and you'll see!
- Jeremiah is a supermodel!
- You wouldn't have guessed.
I'm not surprised that Jeremiah
thinks being a model
be very important, a big secret
which he cannot reveal.
This is what is expected
of the Beauty tribe.
So I decided
to return the favor.
I also have something to say.
Good...
- So...
- You have the idol.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- For a week.
- It's not true!
I told Tasha and Jeremiah
about my idol,
because it's time to go for it,
roll the dice, take a risk.
If it works,
it's a new chance.
The game is not over.
So who are we voting for tonight?
- Wow.
- Why Woo and not Tony?
It is the most dangerous
in the tests.
OK.
I can play it for me,
I can play it for Jeremiah,
I can keep it.
But if I use it wrong,
I could bite
my fingers all my life.
Now here are
the members of the jury.
Sarah, Morgan, and LJ,
eliminated at the last board.
Spencer, at the last tip,
it seemed
that Tasha, Jeremiah and you
were in trouble,
and then LJ was eliminated
by surprise.
Is the game open?
It was for a while,
but we three know
what to expect.
We are the minority.
Jeremiah, are you
okay with that?
Yes. We were in reward yesterday,
we chatted a bit with Jefra,
trying to see if we could
turn the game around.
But she decided
to go back with them.
Jefra, you seem
to be very impressionable.
I was still a little bitter
about this story with LJ,
and wondered
about my place in my covenant.
And Jeff, the three of us,
we didn't know.
- Trish, Kass and me.
- It wasn't just her.
- All of them, we didn't know.
- So to be honest, Jeff,
I started
considering my options.
And I prefer
risk being eliminated
by this alliance,
rather than going to the finals
with Tasha or Spencer,
who would probably beat me.
Spencer, you're disgusted.
It's frustrating.
If I was left out of the vote,
I wouldn't come back to the camp
wondering about my place.
I'll come back to camp knowing
that I'm aloof,
and down the covenant.
Tony swore on his wife
and his kid, on everyone.
He broke many of those promises.
It will break others.
Jefra is right, now is the time
to step back
and examine who you are playing with.
Can you specify
which promise I broke?
- You broke a lot. Towards LJ...
- Precise.
And I don't blame you for that.
- I know, but...
- I did too, and I lied.
- I'm just saying that.
- I didn't break a promise.
And there's a reason for that.
Let's put it another way.
If Tony and any
of you go all the way,
- my vote will go to Tony.
- Mine too.
Because Tony ran this game,
and you didn't.
Woo, is that good
news or bad news
what three potential jurors say
that if Tony goes to the final,
he has three votes?
Yeah, those three are
for Tony, and if he goes all the way,
they could vote for him.
But he will only succeed
with our help.
I'm not for Tony,
I'm for me.
I'm just saying I think Tony
make sure
you are in a position to win.
We had
a discussion today that you know nothing about.
We criticized Tony
for having it both ways.
We said
it didn't suit us.
No one looks alarmed.
- It's the case.
- That's why we talked to him.
He said he was gonna
stop bullshitting
and I hope he heard us.
- Absolutely, absolutely.
- High and loud.
Jeff, in this game,
you have to make big moves.
But at the right time.
Timing is crucial.
Now, that would be inconsistent.
At this stage of the game,
we must stay united to move forward.
At this point, let them say,
"Come back with us!",
it would be inconsistent.
So if it's five against three,
and Tasha being immune,
Woo, how do you decide
between Spencer and Jeremiah?
We examined the possibilities
whether one or the other has an idol.
This is the greatest danger
at this stage.
So it's going to be tough.
' Cause we might
vote for a guy
who is going to play an idol.
Jeremiah, the discussions
are quite frank,
and you're pretty
sure it's you or Spencer tonight.
What are you doing to divert
the attention from you, to Spencer?
Spencer is very dangerous.
I would eliminate him,
but he's my boyfriend.
He's probably
more dangerous than me.
-Spencer.
- Yeah.
How do you react?
He does what he has to do.
Yes, I don't blame him
for giving these arguments.
I may be perceived
as dangerous.
But you also have to
consider social play.
He's one of the nicest guys
that I have ever met.
Tasha, how do you decide
who to vote for?
Honestly, last time
we voted for Tony,
knowing that we would not beat them.
And that pissed him off, so...
- I wasn't mad.
- We're not voting Tony tonight.
- We'll pick someone and...
- You can't vote Tony,
because I brought my bag of tricks,
as usual.
- Yeah, so we'll pick someone.
- Nope?
And we'll stick to it, Jeff.
I don't see you taking
anything out of your bag.
Spencer, Tony is talking about
his bag of tricks again, and you laugh.
I never leave
camp without him, Jeff.
I do not know.
I don't know what he has in his bag.
I would like to find out,
but I haven't had the chance.
Well, it's time to vote.
Kass, it's up to you.
Bro,
this vote sucks a lot, man!
You see!
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
You can steal
all the clues you want from me, Woo.
I have it for real.
It's not a real one.
He is indeed an immunity idol.
Votes against Spencer
will not count.
You see the inexperience
of this young boy?
He was going to give his idol to Jeremy.
He thought I was going
to use mine.
Who is Jeremy?
By the way, it's a fake idol.
Good. I will read the votes.
First vote.
Woo.
Three votes Woo.
Jeremiah.
- Sorry, mate.
- No problem.
Jeremiah, equality.
Three votes Jeremiah,
three votes Woo.
Four votes Jeremiah,
Tenth person eliminated
and fourth member of the jury:
Jeremiah.
Bring me your torch.
- Jeremiah, the tribe has spoken.
- Yup.
Goodbye everyone.
Another piece of advice with a big blow.
Sometimes it works, sometimes it doesn't.
But if you want to win,
you have to keep doing it.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
In the next episode of Survivor...
To eat!
Welcome to Survivor Auctions.
While everyone
is focused on auctions,
When she said she wanted to kill you,
she wasn't lying.
...to change the game.
If I can make Tony paranoid,
it's gold.
It will be chaos
tonight, my friend.
For some reason,
they targeted me.
Spencer did
what he had to do, run away.
I thought I would make a million.
I think I played very well.
I think I could have
gone all the way.
But what do you want...
At 34, I had never
done anything like this.
I'm glad I
had the opportunity
to come here and compete.
I did my best.