>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," FOR KEITH,
EVERYTHING WAS GOING RIGHT.
>> HECK, YEAH.
>> Jeff: HE FOUND A CLUE TO A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AND AFTER
PROTECTING VAL AT EXILE, HE
GAINED AN ALLY IN HER HUSBAND
JEREMY.
>> I OWE YOU ANYWAY.
>> HE'S A FIREFIGHTER.
I'M A FIREFIGHTER.
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT IS A
BROTHERHOOD.
>> Jeff: BUT THE REST OF HIS
TRIBE WAS STRUGGLING.
>> WE HAVE LOST OUR FLINT.
>> Jeff: JOHN LOST THE FLINT
AND DREW SIMPLY LOST HIS ENERGY.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW YOU
COME ON HERE AND YOU DON'T PULL
YOU OWN WEIGHT.
>> Jeff: BUT AT THE LAST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE --
COME ON, GUYS!
-- THEY BEAT COYOPA AGAIN.
HUNAHPU WINS FOR THE THIRD
STRAIGHT TIME.
AND FINALLY JOHN R'S PAST CAUGHT
UP WITH HIM.
>> IF YOU WERE A MAN, I WOULD
KNOCK YOUR TEETH OUT.
>> JOHN!
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
COYOPA CONTINUED TO FALL APART.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD THROW ONE
OF THE GUYS OUT.
>> Jeff: THE MEN'S ALLIANCE
CRUMBLED.
AND JOHN WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
BLIND SIDED.
>> WELL PLAYED.
>> Jeff: 15 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> WE GOT RID OF THE ATHLETE,
BUT WE WEREN'T WINNING ANYWAY.
>> AT TRIBAL JOHN GOT VOTED OUT.
YEAH.
KUDOS TO THE TEAM.
HE WAS THE BIGGEST, STRONGEST
GUY ON OUR TRIBE, BUT I FEEL
LIKE MORE IMPORTANTLY YOU HAVE
TO HAVE A POSITIVE TEAM, SO
JOHN'S ATTITUDE, BEING REMOVED,
WILL HELP US.
UNFORTUNATELY THAT LEAVES DALE
ON THE OUTS.
>> DALE, I PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
TOLD YOU THAT'S WHAT WE WERE
DOING, BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU
WOULD HAVE DONE.
>> PROBABLY NOT MUCH I COULD
HAVE DONE.
I'M NOT TRYING TO DEFEND JOHN.
HE TOLD ME RIGHT OFF THE BAT, I
HAVE A SHORT TEMPER, ALWAYS
HAVE.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT WE ARE.
>> I PROBABLY GET COMFORTABLE IN
OUR FIVE-GUY ALLIANCE AND LET
THE SOCIAL GAME SLIDE.
I HAVE TO PUT MORE EFFORT INTO
BUILDING TRUST WITH PEOPLE.
BECAUSE AS OF NOW, IF WE LOSE
THE NEXT INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
I'M TOAST.
>> HAVE A SEAT.
>> AWESOME.
>> OH, MAN.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I JUST FOLLOWED -- FOUND THE
FLINT.
>> NO WAY?
>> IT WAS RIGHT HERE.
>> I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE WE WERE
THAT DUMB THE LEAVE IT IN THE
FIRE PIT.
I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE I WAS THAT
DUMB.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'M HAPPY OR
VERY MAD.
>> THE OTHER DAY WE LOST OUR
FINT AND WE HAD TO FORFEIT OUR
FISHING GEAR TO GET NEW ONE.
IT REALLY AGGRAVATED ME BECAUSE
I'M A BIG FISHERMAN.
I DEFINITELY COULD PROVIDE FOR
THE TRIBE, BUT NOW I'M LITERALLY
STARVING TO DEATH.
WE NEED THAT FISHING GEAR.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> CAN WE BARTER WITH JEFF?
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO TRADE IT
BACK.
>> I DON'T THINK HE'LL BARTER.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> DREW'S A LOT OF TALK, LET'S
BE HONEST.
HE SAYS HE CAN DO ALL THESE
AMAZING THINGS AND THEN HE
SLEEPS FOR FOUR HOURS.
ALL WE KEEP HEARING FROM GEAR,
FISHING GEAR, FISHING GEAR, WE
SHOULD HAVE GOT THE FISHING
GEAR.
>> THE FISHING GEAR IS GONE.
IT'S NOT LIKE EVERY TIME WE GET
THE CHOOSE FISHING GEAR.
>> EATING THE SAME PORTIONS AT A
100-POUND GIRL IS REALLY KILLING
ME, SO I THINK I'LL BE BALLS UP
AND SAY, WORK WITH ME, JEFF.
THAT'S WHAT A GOOD LEADER DOES.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE DECISIONS THAT
NOBODY ELSE HAS TO DO.
IT'S HARD TO DRAG THESE PEOPLE
ALONG AND NOT GET MUCH IN
RETURN, BUT THE THING, IS
WITHOUT ME, THESE PEOPLE WOULD
BE NOTHING.
YOU KNOW?
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
HUNAHPU GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW COYOPA TRIBE.
JOHN VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
JULIE, YOUR TRIBE APPLAUDED.
THEY STOOD UP.
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED.
I'VE KIND OF CREATED A SHELL
BECAUSE I SAW KIND OF HOW HE WAS
GOING THE PLAY THE GAME, AND I
KNEW IF HE CONTINUED THAT WAY I
HAD TO JUST BE BLIND TO IT AND
BE HERE WITH MY TEAM AND STAND
ON MY OWN TWO FEET.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
NEXT REWARD CHALLENGE?
ONE THING BEFORE WE GET GOING...
WAIT.
DO YOU HAVE THE FLINT IN YOUR
HAND.
>> NOBODY ELSE ON MY TEAM HAD
THE COURAGE TO BRING THIS UP.
WE FOUND OUR OTHER FLINT.
THIS ONE HASN'T...
>> FANTASTIC.
>> LISTEN.
THIS ONE HAS NOT BEEN STRUCK ONE
TIME.
I WAS WONDERING IF THERE WAS
SOME REASONABLE TRADE WE COULD
DO, MAYBE HALF THE FISHING GEAR,
MAYBE JUST A MASK, A SNORKEL AND
A SPEAR, JUST SOMETHING TO PUT
SOME FOOD ON THE TABLE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: NOW BECAUSE THIS ONE
IS CITY BRAND-NEW, BASICALLY
STRAIGHT OUT OF THE BOX, YOU
WANT TO MAKE A RETURN?
>> WHAT'S YOUR RETURN POLICY,
JEFF?
>> Jeff: WELL, IT SOUNDS
REASONABLE.
>> EXACTLY.
>>
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE TAUNTING
US.
>> Jeff: I AM TAUNTING YOU.
PUT THE FLINT BACK.
YOU MADE THE TRADE.
SHALL WE GET TO REWARD?
ONE PERSON FROM EACH TRIBE WILL
USE A GRAPPLING HOOK TO RETRIEVE
THREE BAGS OF BALLS.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE BALLS, YOU
WILL THEN USE A CATAPULT TO
LAUNCH THOSE BALLS INTO A SERIES
OF FIVE BASKETS.
FIRST PERSON TO GET ONE BALL IN
EACH BASKET WINS REWARD FOR
THEIR TRIBE.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> ONCE AGAIN YOU HAVE A CHOICE.
ALL THE COMFORT ITEMS, HAMMOCK,
BLANKET, PILLOWS, OR SOMETHING
THAT MIGHT BE A LITTLE MORE
APPETIZING, CAMPFIRE FOOD --
SAUSAGE, POPCORN, S'MORES.
GREAT WAY TO CELEBRATE A
VICTORY.
>> YES, YES, YES.
>> Jeff: WE'RE GOING TO ROCK,
PAPER, SCISSOR TO SEE WHO GETS
THE ADVANTAGE OF PUTTING UP
FIRST.
PAPER COVERS ROCK.
HUNAHPU GETS THE ADVANTAGE OF
PUTTING UP FIRST.
JON IS GOING TO GO UP AGAINST
JACLYN.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
IT IS GIRLFRIEND VERSUS
BOYFRIEND.
EXILE ISLAND FOR THE LOSER.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
JACLYN OUT FIRST.
JACLYN WITH A NICE TOSS.
THAT SHOULD BRING BACK ONE BAG.
JACLYN HAS HER FIRST BAG.
JON A LITTLE SHORT.
>> THAT'S A GIRL'S THROW, JON.
>> Jeff: NOW THE TAUNTING
BEGINS.
>> LOVE YOUR DAD, KELLEY.
>> GIVE ANOTHER GOOD TOSS, GIRL.
>> Jeff: JACLYN WITH ANOTHER
NICE TOSS.
JACLYN HAS HER SECOND BAG.
JON STILL WORKING ON HIS FIRST.
DOES HE HAVE IT?
YES.
JON HAS ONE.
CAN HE GET TWO?
JUST MISSED IT.
JON WITH HIS FIRST BAG.
>> NOW BIG TOSS.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: JACLYN JUST MISSES ON
HER THIRD BAG.
JON WITH ANOTHER NICE TOSS.
THIS SHOULD BE HIS SECOND BAG.
AND IT IS.
>> THERE WE GO.
THERE WE GO.
>> Jeff: WE ARE TIED.
>> QUICK, QUICK, QUICK, QUICK!
>> Jeff: JON WITH ANOTHER GOOD
TOSS.
CAN HE HOOK HIS THIRD BAG RIGHT
HERE?
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: JON HAS HIS THIRD
BAG.
JACLYN, CAN SHE MAKE THIS ONE
WORK?
NO.
JON STARTING TO UNTIE.
>> JON, YOU GOT IT.
YOU'RE AHEAD.
>> Jeff: JACLYN HAS SOME GREAT
MOMENTUM, BUT IT IS GONE.
JON GOING TO LAUNCH HIS FIRST
BALL.
>> YOU GOT TO GET A FEEL FOR IT.
>> Jeff: TAKING AIM.
>> COME ON, JON-JON.
>> Jeff: JUST A LITTLE FAR.
>> SOFT, JON.
>> Jeff: JON SCORES HIS FIRST
POINT.
HUNAHPU HAS ONE.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, NICE TOSS.
JACLYN HAS HER THIRD BAG.
JON WITH HIS SECOND POINT.
JACLYN'S GOT TO PICK IT UP NOW.
JON HAS A TWO-POINT LEAD.
GOING FOR HIS THIRD, TAKING AIM.
NICE LITTLE KICK.
JUST A LITTLE MUCH.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
YOU GOT TO START SHOOTING THEM.
>> Jeff: JACLYN WITH HER FIRST
SHOT.
JACLYN IN AND OUT.
JON WITH HIS THIRD POINT.
COYOPA ONCE AGAIN FALLING
BEHIND.
JACLYN IS STILL LOOKING FOR HER
FIRST.
THERE IT IS.
JACLYN HAS HER FIRST POINT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
JON WITH HIS FOURTH.
JON DOWN TO ONE LEFT.
IT IS THE MOST DIFFICULT ONE ON
THE COURSE.
JACLYN SCORES HER SECOND POINT.
>> GO, JACLYN, GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: JACLYN NEEDS TO LAND
ANOTHER ONE QUICKLY.
JON FOR THE WIN.
JUST MISSES.
>> SO CLOSE.
>> YOU'RE STILL IN IT.
YOU'RE STILL IN IT.
>> Jeff: JACLYN WITH HER THIRD
POINT.
QUICKLY DWAYNEING ON JON.
JACLYN CAN TIE IT UP RIGHT HERE.
JACLYN SCORES HER FOURTH.
WE'RE TIED 4-4!
THE FIRST IN THE BASKET WINS.
JON IN AND OUT OF THAT CENTER
BASKET.
>> THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL, THOUGH.
>> Jeff: JACLYN JUST MISSES
FOR COYOPA.
IT'S A RACE BACK NOW.
WHO WILL GET THE BALL IN THE AIR
FIRST.
THAT COULD BE THE DIFFERENCE.
JON SLIPTION AND FALLS OFF,
OPENING THE DOOR FOR JACLYN ONCE
AGAIN.
JACLYN FOR THE WIN.
JACLYN JUST MISSES.
JON COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE,
SEND HIS GIRLFRIEND TO EXILE
ISLAND.
JON SCORES FOR HUNAHPU.
HUNAHPU WINS REWARD AND JON
SENDS HIS GIRLFRIEND TO EXILE
ISLAND.
>> JACLYN, THAT WAS SO GOOD.
>> Jeff: JON, YOU KNOW YOU'RE
SENDING YOUR GIRLFRIEND TO EXILE
ISLAND.
YOU'VE HEARD THE STORIES.
IT'S NOT PLEASANT.
>> IT'S HARD TO SEND HER BECAUSE
OF WHERE SHE'S GOING.
IT'S NOT EASY.
BUT SHE CAN HANDLE IT.
>> OH, YEAH, I CAN HANDLE IT OUT
THERE.
I MEAN, I'M AFRAID IT'S GOING TO
RAIN.
I HEARD THERE'S IN SHELTER.
>> Jeff: IT'S A FACT.
>> WELL, THERE'S NO SHELTER AND
IT'S REALLY STORMY LOOKING RIGHT
NOW.
>> Jeff: BUT IT DOESN'T HURT
YOUR FEELINGS THAT HE SAYS SHE
CAN HANDLE IT?
>> I LIKE THE RESPECTS.
IF HE WAS SCARED OUT OF HIS
MIND, IT WOULD DISCREDIT ME.
>> SHE'S ABLE TO TAKE CARE OF
HERSELF, THAT'S WHY WE HAVE SUCH
A GREAT RELATIONSHIP, BECAUSE WE
CAN CARE FOR EACH OTHER SO MUCH.
>> THANKS.
>> Jeff: SO BIG DECISION YOU
HAVE THE MAKE.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO PICK FROM
YOUR TRIBE TO GO TO EXILE?
DREW IS SAYING HE WANTS TO DO
IT.
>> I TRUST DREW.
HE PULLS HIS WEIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, DREW.
COME ON DOWN.
>> THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
DREW, JACLYN, YOU WILL HEAD TO
EXILE ISLAND.
YOU WILL RETURN IN TIME FOR THE
NEXT EXILE CHALLENGE.
HERE'S YOUR MAP.
GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE, JACLYN.
>> GOOD JOB, DREW.
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU, YOU HAVE
DOMINATED, LOSING JUST ONE
REWARD CHALLENGE.
ANOTHER BIG DECISION.
YOU HAVE INSTANT GRATIFICATION
HERE.
FOOD.
OR YOU HAVE LONG-TERM
PROTECTION.
>> COMFORT.
>> YEAH, LONG TERM.
>> YOU'RE GOING THE CHOOSE
COMFORT?
>> WE HAVE TO GET SOMETHING WE
CAN SHARE WITH DREW WHEN HE
COMES BACK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HUNAHPU, COME GET YOUR REWARD.
HEAD OUT.
COYOPA, ONCE AGAIN, HAVE NOTHING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK THE
CAMP.
>> WE'RE DYING TO WIN.
I WANT TO WIN SO BAD.
WE'RE DESPERATE AND CONTINUING
TO LOSE, WE'RE ON THE ROPES.
YOU KNOW, ARE WE GOING TO BE
ABLE TO PICK OURSELVES UP OR ARE
WE GOING TO BE THE WORST TRIBE
IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY?
WHO KNOWS.
>> I THOUGHT THAT WAS GOING TO
BE SO MUCH HARDER THAN IT WAS,
SENDING HER TO EXILE, BUT THEN
WHEN I LOOKED AT HER AND SHE'S
SMILING, SHE WAS FINE.
>> YEAH, SHE'S SUPER TOUGH.
>> SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> I HAVE MIXED EMOTIONS ON HOW
I FEEL ABOUT SENDING DREW AND
JACLYN TO EXILE.
HE IS SOMEBODY WHO I DO TRUST,
BUT IF DREW IS ANYTHING LIKE HE
IS AT CAMP, JACLYN MIGHT BE
DOING MOST OF THE FIREWOOD
COLLECTING.
BUT SHE'S VERY STRONG, SO I
THINK SHE CAN HANDLE SOMEBODY
LIKE DREW.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY DID IT.
>> WHAT?
>> KICKED JOHN OUT.
>> I'M SHOCKED.
IT'S TOUGH TO SEE HIM GO.
IT'S PLAYING THAT WAY, I'M GLAD
I DON'T HAVE TO BE A BYSTANDER
ANYMORE.
MOVE ON AND LET ME PLAY THE GAME
AND NOT HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT HIM.
I'M GOOD.
SEEING MY BOYFRIEND JOHN VOTED
OUT WAS HURTFUL JUST TO KNOW
THAT EVERYBODY'S JUST ANTI-JOHN
ROCKER, WHO IS THE LOVE OF MY
LIFE, BUT THINGS LIKE THIS
HAPPEN ALL THE TIME WITH JOHN,
WHERE HE'S AUTOMATICALLY JUDGED
FROM DAY ONE.
SO I KIND OF PREPARED MYSELF.
BUT TO BE WITHOUT HIM RIGHT NOW
IS SUCH A DESPERATE FEELING.
ALL I CAN DO IS JUST TRY MY BEST
AND GET MYSELF BACK IN THE GAME.
>> BEING ON EXILE ISLAND SUCKS
BECAUSE IT'S SO HOT AND THERE'S
NO SHELTER.
IT'S ROUGH OUT HERE.
I'LL GO RIGHT, YOU GO LEFT?
>> OKAY.
>> I GOT IT THE GOOD THING ABOUT
BEING HERE WITH JACLYN IS I GET
AN AWESOME CLUE.
THAT'S NUMBER ONE.
NUMBER TWO, I GOT A PRETTY MISS
MICHIGAN-TYPE LOOKING CHICK OUT
HERE.
>> YOU'RE A LADIES MAN.
[INAUDIBLE]
>> IT SEEMS TO BE A CURSE.
THE FACT THAT I'M A LADIES' MAN
SEEMS TO WORK TO MY ADVANTAGE,
BUT I HAVEN'T BEEN TRYING TO
WORK THAT ANGLE TOO MUCH.
JACLYN IS DEFINITELY VERY
ATTRACTIVE LOOKING, BUT I'M NOT
OUT HERE LOOKING FOR LOVE,
DEFINITELY NOT WITH ONE OF MY
BUDDY'S GIRLS.
I'M REALLY JUST OUT HERE TRYING
THE STRATEGIZE AND MANIPULATE
MINDS.
THERE'S REALLY NOBODY THAT'S
PHYSICALLY BETTER THAN JON AND I
ON OUR TEAM HONESTLY, BUT I'M
SCEPTICAL ABOUT THE GIRLS VOTING
US OUT, SO THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET
THERE, ONE DAY AT A TIME.
>> ALEX TOLD ME HIS BROTHER'S A
LADIES' MAN, SO I'M LIKE, OH,
GOD, BUT I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT
HIM.
I'M JUST THINKING ABOUT THE
GAME.
SO I JUST WANT THE KIND OF
FIGURE OUT WITH DREW WHAT'S
GOING ON AND COLLABORATE.
SOMETHING'S GOING THE HAPPEN
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, IF WE LOSE
AGAIN...
>> WE CAN'T LET YOU GUYS LOSE
AGAIN.
WE SHOULD THROW THE NEXT GAME.
>> ARE YOU CONSIDERING THAT?
>> THERE'S SNAKES ON OUR TEAM
THAT HAVE TO GO.
I DECIDED TO THROW THE NEXT
IMMUNE 2EU CHALLENGE BECAUSE ALL
OF THE GIRLS IN MY TRIBE SEEM
UNTRUSTWORTHY TO ME.
THEY KNOW IN THE LONG RUN THEY
HAVE NO CHANCE TO COMPETE
AGAINST US.
I'D LIKE THE START WHITTLING
DOWN THE PEOPLE ON OUR TRIBE SO
I CAN GET MYSELF FORWARD AND WIN
THE MILLION DOLLARS.
>> OH, YEAH.
I COULD GET USED TO THIS.
>> THE OTHER DAY ON EXILE
ISLAND, I GOT A CLUE THERE WAS
AN IDOL OVER HERE BY THE WELL,
SO I WENT UP HERE DIGGED AROUND,
KICKED AROUND TO SEE IF I
COULDN'T FIND IT.
I DUG AROUND THE SAND FOR ABOUT
30 MINUTES, AND I THOUGHT, I'M
WASTING MY TIME.
UNFORTUNATELY IT LOOK LIKE I'M A
DAY LATE AND A DOLLAR SHORT.
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY'S ALREADY
BEEN THROUGH THERE, SO I'M
THINKING I MIGHT HAVE GOT BEAT
TO THE PUNCH.
GUYS, HERE'S THE DEAL, I'VE GOT
A CLUE, AND I KIND OF POKED
AROUND JUST A FEW MINUTES AGO,
AND I DIDN'T FIND NOTHING.
THE ONLY OTHER PERSON THAT COULD
FIND IT IS THE PERSON THAT WENT
TO EXILE ISLAND BEFORE ME, AND
THAT'S JEREMY.
SO JEREMY'S GOT AN IDOL.
KEEP THAT IN MIND.
>> NO, HE DID NOT?
NO, HE DID NOT.
WHO DID HE TELL?
>> I'M THINKING I HAVE KEITH
WITH ME, BUT NOW I FIND OUT HE'S
TELLING EVERYBODY THAT I HAVE
THE IDOL.
I WANT YOU ALL THE WATCH KEITH,
LIKE WATCH HIM SEARCHING ALL UP
IN HERE.
I SAW THAT, TOO.
HE GOT THE CLUE, AND THEN HE'S
GOING THE TRY TO PUT IT ON ME?
HE'S GOT A CLUE.
I'M PISSED.
WE'RE BOTH FIREFIGHTERS.
I TOLD YOU I HAVE YOUR BACK.
IF YOU THINK I HAVE AN IDOL, WHY
DIDN'T YOU JUST COME TO ME?
DON'T YOU THINK THAT WE'RE ON
THE SAME PAGE AND WE COULD HAVE
USED IT TOGETHER.
WHY YOU GOT THE PLAY ME?
I HAD HIS BACK.
KEITH WAS CHILLING.
HE WASN'T ON ANYONE'S RADAR, BUT
NOW I WANT HIM GONE, BECAUSE
KEITH, YOU'RE A RAT.
>> I'VE GOT TO THINKING, IDOLS
ARE IMPORTANT IN THIS GAME.
I THOUGHT, ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WE'LL GO BACK.
MAYBE I WASN'T DUE NORTH OR
SEVEN STEPS, SO I JUST POKED AND
PRODDED AROUND A LITTLE MORE.
IT'S ALREADY DONE BEEN FOUND,
BUT OBVIOUSLY NOT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, IT JUST
KIND OF JUMPED OUT AT ME, KIND
OF SCARED ME.
I'M PROBABLY NOT GOING TO TELL
ANYBODY THAT I HAVE THE IDOL
BECAUSE THE LAST THING I NEED IS
A TARGET ON MY BACK.
I'M NOT A BRAIN SURGEON, BUT IF
EVERYBODY THINKS JEREMY HAS IT,
THAT COULD BE GOOD FOR ME.
>> THROW MAIL.
>> WES!
>> WES, COME HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GO TELL THE OTHER PEOPLE.
>> YOU ARE BEING A WOMAN RIGHT
NOW.
>> WHENEVER SOMETHING COMES LIKE
THAT...
>> I DID NOT.
>> YEAH, YOU DID.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN TO ME.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
ALEC FEELS LIKE A LITTLE BROTHER
SOMETIMES TO ME, EVEN THOUGH
HE'S TWO YEARS OLDER.
HE LIKES TO BOSS ME AROUND A
LITTLE BIT, SO I'VE HAD TO BITE
MY TONGUE A BUNCH.
I'M LIKE, HELLO, I'M NOT YOUR
FLAME.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL WE'LL SEE
ANOTHER ONE LEAVE.
WHO WILL IT BE?
SWIM, RUN, JERUSALEM AND DIVE, A
PRECISION THROW CAN KEEP YOU
ARRIVE.
>> READ IT ONE MORE TIME.
I WANT TO KANSAS TRAIT ON THE
WORDS AGAIN.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT WE
WILL SEE --
>> BAYLOR DOES THINGS THAT GET
ON MY NERVES, AND I'M NOT GOING
TO GET AWAY WITH IT.
SHE MAKES IT SEEMS LIKE IN HER
LIFE EVERYTHING IS GIVEN TO HER,
JUST LIKE FOR DREW, BUT SHE'S
NOT MY BROTHER, SO I'M GOING TO
CALL HER ON EVERY SINGLE THING
SHE DOES.
>> I WANT THAT.
>> WE HAVE THE CLEAN THAT GUY.
>> DO YOU AGREE THAT SOMETHING
NEEDS TO BE CLEANED BEFORE WE
EAT OUT OF IT?
>> DUMP IT OUT AND RUB IT WITH
SAND.
>> YOU WON'T HAVE TO DO IT
TWICE.
>> AS A KID, MY DAD DIDN'T GO
WAKE DREW UP TO GO WASH CARS
BECAUSE HE KNEW DREW WOULDN'T BE
WORTH A DAMN.
HE CAME AND WOKE ME UP.
I HAD TO WORK HARD FOR
EVERYTHING I'VE GOTTEN.
I THINK IN THE END IT'S MADE ME
A STRONGER PERSON.
THAT'S JUST HOW I GREW UP.
>> NO WORRIES.
>> MY DAD JUST CALLED ME ON IT.
ALEC, I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOU
DO THAT.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOU DO
THAT EITHER.
>> THANKS.
>> I THINK SHARING SOME OF THAT
KNOWLEDGE WITH OTHERS MIGHT BE
WHAT WE NEED TO DO, GET
EVERYBODY ON THE SAME PAGE AND
JUST BELIEVE THAT WE CAN BEAT
THE OTHER TRIBE.
DAVID CAN BEAT GOLIATH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
BEFORE WE GET TO THE CHALLENGE,
WE'LL BRING IN DREW AND JACLYN
RETURNING FROM EXILE ISLAND.
>> AM I GOING TO THROW THE
CHALLENGE TODAY?
THAT IS THE MILLION DOLLAR
QUESTION.
PEOPLE WILL HATE ME FOR DOING
THAT, BUT I COULD CARE LESS.
SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO DO WHAT YOU
GOT TO DO TO GET THINGS DONE.
>> WELCOME BACK, GIRL.
>> HI, GUYS.
>> YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAKE BACK THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ONE
PERSON FROM EACH TRIBE WILL SWIM
OUT, RACE UP A PLATFORM, DIVE
INTO THE WATER TO RETRIEVE A
RING, BRING IT BACK.
THEN THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU COLLECT IT, ALL FOUR
RINGS, THE TWO REMAINING TRIBE
MEMBERS WILL ATTEMPT TO LAND
THOSE RINGS ON POSTS.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, IS SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
COYOPA HAS YET TO WIN AN
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
HUNAHPU HAS YET TO LOSE.
HUNAHPU, YOU HAVE THREE EXTRA
PEOPLE, SITTING THREE PEOPLE
OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
KELLEY GOING TO SIT OUT, JON
GOING TO SIT OUT AND JEREMY
GOING TO SIT OUT.
INTERESTING CHOICES.
THREE SITOUTS, YOU'LL JOIN ME
OVER HERE.
EVERYONE ELSE, GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ALL RIGHT, MISSY AND BAYLOR IN
THE WATER FIRST.
MOTHER AND DAUGHTER SQUARING OFF
AGAIN.
>> GET UP THERE.
GO, GO, GO!
JUMP.
YES.
>> COME ON, MISSY.
>> Jeff: BOTH GOING FOR THOSE
FIRST RINGS.
THREE KNOTS, UNTIE THEM AND HEAD
BACK.
BAYLOR HAS HERS.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
MISSY HAS HERS.
>> COME ON, MISSY.
>> COME ON, MISS.
>> Jeff: NOW YOU HAVE THE
CLIMB BACK UP THAT LADDER AND
RACE BACK DOWN THE PLATFORMMENT
BAYLOR RACING BACK WITH THAT
FIRST RING FOR COYOPA.
MISSY RACING BACK WITH FIRST
RING FOR HUNAHPU.
>> OKAY, MISS.
>> HERE WE GO, HERE WE GO, HERE
WE GO.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR'S BACK.
JACLYN NOW IN THE WATER FOR
COYOPA.
REED NOW IN THE WATER FOR
HUNAHPU.
COME ON, JACKIE.
RUN AND JUMP.
>> GO, REED.
>> GO, REED!
>> Jeff: JACLYN AND REED BOTH
HEADING FOR THOSE SECOND RINGS.
IT'S A LITTLE LONGER SWIM THIS
TIME.
REED HAS HIS RING.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
JACLYN HAS HERS.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
>> GO, JACKIE!
COME ON, JAC.
MAKE UP THAT TIME.
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU BACK IN THE
LEAD.
JACLYN BACK IN THE WATER.
REED IS BACK.
NATALIE NOW IN THE WATER FOR
HUNAHPU.
JACLYN BACK.
ALEC IN THE WATER FOR COYOPA.
ALEC PICKING UP A LOT OF TIME.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO IT!
NATALIE WORKING ON THAT THIRD
RING FOR HUNAHPU.
SHE'S GOT IT.
HEADING BACK.
ALEC WORKING ON THE THIRD RING
FOR COYOPA.
HE'S GOT IT.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
>> COME ON, ALEC!
>> Jeff: ALEC HAS MADE UP A
LOT OF TIME IN THIS ROUND.
THEY BOTH COME UP.
WE'RE DEAD EVEN AGAIN.
ALEC NOW PUTS COYOPA BACK IN THE
LEAD.
GET HIM ON THAT PLATFORM.
WES IN THE WATER FOR COYOPA.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: KEITH IN THE WATER
FOR HUNAHPU.
FATHER-SON IN THIS LAST BATTLE
FOR A RING.
THEY'RE NOT MESSING AROUND.
KEITH MOVING QUICKLY IN THE
WATER.
WES HAS THE FOURTH RING FOR
COYOPA.
KEITH HAS THE FOURTH RING FOR
HUNAHPU.
NICES TOs FROM WES.
COYOPA HAS ALL FOUR.
THEY HAVE THEIR TWO REBOUNDERS
IN.
NOW DALE WILL START TOSSING.
KEITH MOVING QUICKLY IN THE
WATER.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THE RING BACK.
KEITH BACK WITH THAT FOURTH RING
FOR HUNAHPU.
HUNAHPU NOW PUTS THEIR
REBOUNDERS IN.
ONE RING AT A TIME.
YOU GOT TO GET THE RING BACK.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: COYOPA SCORES THEIR
FIRST RING.
>> MY SHOT NOW.
NOW IT'S MY SHOT.
>> JUST KEEP FIRING.
>> Jeff: DREW WITH ANOTHER
MISS.
COYOPA SCORES THEIR SECOND RING.
DREW SCORES FOR HUNAHPU.
COYOPA SHORT.
>> SORRY.
>> Jeff: OH, SAME RING.
FIGURE IT OUT.
DREW MISSES AGAIN.
COYOPA SCORES ANOTHER.
COYOPA LEADS WITH THREE.
THEY'RE DOWN TO ONE LEFT.
DREW IS SINGLE HANDEDLY LOSING
THIS FOR HIS TRIBE.
THIS COULD DO IT.
COYOPA, THAT IS IT.
COYOPA WINS THEIR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
>> YES!
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> I KNEW IT!
>> SORRY, GUYS.
>> Jeff: COYOPA, WHO WANTS IT?
>> GRAB IT.
>> Jeff: COYOPA, NO TRIBAL
COUNCIL FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
THIS GAME.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ALL RIGHT.
HUNAHPU, FOR THE FIRST TIME,
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK THE
CAMP.
WE'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> I THREW THE CHALLENGE BECAUSE
WE NEED TO GET SOME OF THE
SNAKES OFF.
IF I DON'T WANT THE WIN, WE'RE
NOT GOING TO WIN.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES ME THE KINGPIN
OF MY TRIBE.
>> HAPPY TO BE HOME?
>> HELL YEAH.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT THAT.
I KIND OF DECIDED IN EXILE IF I
HAD THE OPPORTUNITY TO THROW
THIS GAME I WOULD, AND I DID.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY KNEW I WAS
THROWING IT, BUT I COULD CARE
LESS BECAUSE WE NEED THE START
GETTING RID OF SOME OF THE
SNAKES ON OUR TRIBE.
SO BASICALLY I'M A BAD ASS AND
THE MANIPULATOR OF THIS GAME.
OKAY.
HERE'S MY IDEA.
I'M WORRIED THAT GOING INTO THE
MERGE, INDIVIDUALS ARE GOING TO
OUTNUMBER COUPLES, SO WE TAKE
PEOPLE THAT DON'T HAVE A LOVED
ONE OUT.
THAT'S WHY I THINK JULIE IS A
VERY EASY VOTE AND SHE HURTS OUR
TEAM.
>> EXACTLY.
>> MY ARGUMENT TODAY IS JULIE
SHOULD BE THE ONE TO GO.
SHE HASN'T BEEN HELPING IN
CHALLENGES.
SHE DOESN'T HELP AROUND CAMP.
IT WOULD BE AN EASY ONE TO AGREE
ON.
BUT MOST IMPORTANTLY SHE DOES
NOT HAVE A LOVED ONE.
>> OKAY.
I'M GOING TO TARGET JULIE.
THIS IS MY REASON.
RIGHT NOW THERE'S NO REASON TO
VOTE WITH US RIGHT NOW.
>> LISTEN TO ME FIRST.
>> OKAY, GUYS, LISTEN.
AMONGST US, SHE'S THE MOST
DANGEROUS PERSON IN THIS TRIBE.
WHO IS IT?
WHO IS GOING TO MANIPULATE THIS
GAME AND THROW THE STRONGER GUYS
OUT?
IT'S KELLEY.
DONE DEAL.
LOOK AT WHAT HAPPENS...
>> SHE KNOWS THE GAME.
>> LOOK WHAT HAPPENS IF WE HAVE
KELLEY?
YOU THINK JULIE'S GOING TO BEAT
US?
MY PERSONAL BIGGEST THREAT RIGHT
NOW IS KELLEY.
SHE PLAYS VERY LOW KEY, BUT AT
THE SAME TIME, SHE'S VERY
OBSERVANT.
IF YOU TALK TO HER, YOU KNOW
THAT SHE'S NOT MISSED ONE
EPISODE OF "SURVIVOR."
SO KELLEY IS A THREAT.
AND IT'S MY MISSION TO GET
PEOPLE TO VOTE FOR HER TONIGHT.
>> LISTEN, HERE'S THE DEAL,
KEITH IS TRYING TO GET ME OUT.
KEITH COMES BACK FROM EXILE
SAYING THAT I GOT THE IDOL.
WE NEED TO HAVE EACH OTHER'S
BACKS.
IF SOMEONE'S AFTER YOU, I GO
AFTER THAT PERSON.
IF SOMEONE'S AFTER ME, I PEKO
THE SAME THING.
>> HE'S NOT GOING TO GET YOU.
WHO IS HE GOING TO PERSUADE?
>> YOU'RE OVERLOOKING THE
MASTERMIND HERE.
>> THIS IS THE THING, I WANT
KEITH GONE.
KEITH IS TRYING TO GO AFTER ME,
SO NOW I DON'T TRUST HIM AT ALL.
BUT DREW, HE WANTS TO GET RID OF
KELLEY NOW BECAUSE HE THINKS
KELLEY RUNS THE GIRL, WHICH IS
RIDICULOUS.
SHE'S NOT DOING ANYTHING.
KEITH'S FIRST, YOUR SECOND, I'M
THIRD, YOU'RE FOURTH.
IT'S NOD GOOD LOGIC.
>> WHEN YOU'RE SAYING, THIS
YOU'RE DELG ME YOU DON'T HAVE MY
BACK.
>> YOU'RE WAY TOO EMOTIONAL
ABOUT THIS, JEREMY.
>> GET YOUR BOY, DOG.
WITH DREW THERE'S NO THROWING
BACK AND FORTH.
HE'S JUST LIKE, KELLEY'S GOING
HOME, AND THAT'S IT.
AND IT PISSED ME OFF.
>> I WAS JUST TALKING THE DREW,
AND HE'S LIKE, THE GIRLS ARE
TRYING TO GET THE GUYS OUT.
DREW SAID THAT.
I SAID, THAT'S MESSED UP.
HE TOLD ME, ME, YOU...
>> HE JUST TOLD YOU THAT?
>> I SAID, THERE'S NO GUY-GIRL
THING HERE.
WE HAVE NO POWER.
THAT'S STRAIGHT UP WHAT I TOLD
HIM.
>> DREW, HE'S SCARED THE GIRLS
ARE GOING TO VOTE OUT GUYS,
WHICH IS STUPID.
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE THE NUMBERS
TO DO THAT, BUT THAT'S CONVINCED
OF THIS GIRL-GIRL ALLIANCE.
THE GUYS ARE A MESS.
THEY'RE NOT ON THE SAME PAGE,
WHICH IS GOOD.
IN THE LONG RUN, WHO IS WINNING
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES?
>> DREW OR JOHN.
>> PROBABLY DREW MORE THAN JOHN.
>> MAYBE WE GET RID OF DREW
FIRST.
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> GETTING RID OF DREW, THAT
WOULD BE SO SWEET IF WE CAN PULL
THIS OFF.
>> HE'S SO ANNOYING.
WE HAVE TO DO IT NOW, WHILE THE
GUYS ARE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> WE'RE SENDING KELLEY HOME.
THAT'S IT.
THINK ABOUT IT, GUYS.
I'M TELLING YOU.
LET'S GET KELLEY OUT TONIGHT AND
THEN ALL THESE BITCHES DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO OTHER THAN COME
TO US.
TRUST ME, GUYS.
TRUST ME.
COUNT ON IT.
LOOK ME IN THE EYES.
>> I WAS STANDING BY THE SHELTER
AND I HEARD DREW LEADING THIS
CHARGE TO GET ME OUT, AND I WAS
LYING, WHAT THE HELL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS, MAYBE
HE'S JUST THREATENED BY ME AS A
STRONG FEMALE.
BUT DREW GETS THIS VISION IN HIS
HEAD, AND HE'S LIKE THE KING OF
IT, AND HE HAS TO BE THE ONE
TO... HE HAS TO MAKE THE FINAL
DECISION.
AND I THINK PEOPLE ARE GETTING
OVER THAT REALLY, RALLY QUICKLY.
>> GET RID OF DREW.
WE CAN COME IN STRONG AND SAY
DREW IS TAKING DOWN THE WRONG
GIRL.
>> THIS IS HOW IT'S GOING RIGHT
NOW.
THE GIRLS WANT TO GET RID OF
DREW.
YES, HE'S A MORON, BUT THAT'S A
BIG MOVE.
AND IT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
>> WE'RE SENDING KELLEY HOME.
THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING.
YOU ON BOARD WITH IT OR NOT.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> I'M JUST TELLING YOU THE
TRUTH.
>> DUDE, I DON'T CARE.
>> THE PROBLEM IS, THE GUYS ARE
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
DREW IS SAYING, KELLEY'S THE
PLAYER.
JOHN IS LIKE, WE'RE GOING AFTER
JULIE, AND I WANT TO GET RID OF
KEITH.
>> WELL, WELL, WELL, EVERYBODY
SEEMS TO HAVE THEIR OWN OPINION,
DON'T THEY?
>> IT'S JUST CRAZY.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GET RID OF DREW.
HE'S DIGGING HIS OWN GRAVE, BUT
I'M JUST NOT SURE IF IT'S THE
RIGHT TIME.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD, GREAT BRITAIN -- GRAB
A TORCH, DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN THE FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
OKAY.
OUR FIRST CHANCE TO TALK.
SO CATCH ME UP.
JULIE, TELL ME ABOUT
RELATIONSHIPS.
WHO DO YOU NOTICE IS GETTING
ALONG RIGHT OUT OF THE GATE IN
>> I WOULD HAVE TO SAY JOHN AND
DREW.
THEY RUN AROUND LIKE THEY'RE
FIVE-YEAR-OLDS.
IT'S CUTE.
YEAH.
>> MISSY, WHO DOESN'T GET ALONG?
>> MY OBSERVATION IS THAT WE
HAVE A WHOLE WILL THE OF CHIEFS
AND NOT VERY MANY INDIAN, AND
THEY'RE SELFISH AND SELFLESS
PEOPLE AROUND CAMP.
>> Jeff: HOW MANY SELFISH
PEOPLE DO YOU HAVE ON THIS
TRIBE?
>> HALF THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: DREW, ONE OF THE BAD
THINGS ABOUT WINNING IS YOU
DON'T GET TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
THINGS ARE WITHIN THE TRIBE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
EVERYBODY HAS BEEN PLAYING NICE
UNTIL WE LOST TODAY, JEFF.
I FELT IT RIGHT AFTER THE
CHALLENGE, LIKE WOW WE ACTUALLY
HAVE TO PLAY THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: DREW, LET'S TALK
ABOUT GAME TIME TODAY, BECAUSE I
THOUGHT IT WAS INTERESTING THAT
FOR A TRIBE THAT'S DOMINATED,
THAT YOU GOT DEMOLISHED TODAY,
BY A GUY THAT COULD BE MAYBE
YOUR GRANDDAD.
>> COULD WE HAVE HAD BETTER
SWIMMERS, BETTER RETRIEVERS.
YOU WIN SOME, YOU LOSE SOME.
I DID THE BEST I COULD AND
THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: JOHN, AFTER THE
CHALLENGE, YOU HEAD BACK THE
CAMP.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WE GOT BACK AND PEOPLE JUST
STARTED SCRAMBLING, LIKE, OKAY,
WHAT'S THE VOTE GOING TO BE?
EMOTIONS GOT HIGH, TOO.
IT WAS CONFUSING.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, JON SAYS
EMOTIONS GOT HIGH.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> WELL, SO, I'M JUST GOING TO
SAY IT.
KEITH COMES BACK FROM EXILE AND
TELLS EVERYBODY THAT I HAVE AN
IDOL.
SO I SAY, KEITH, WHY DON'T YOU
COME TO ME AND SAY, HEY, DO YOU
HAVE AN IDOL.
WE'RE ALIGNED.
>> I WAS LOOKING FOR THE IDOL
AND I DIDN'T FIND THE IDOL.
I ASSUMED, MIGHT HAVE BEEN
WRONG, I ASSUMED JEREMY HAD BEAT
ME TO THE PUNCH.
>> AND I'M IN YOUR ALLIANCE, SO
WHY DON'T YOU COME TO ME?
>> BECAUSE YOU GO TO SOMEBODY
ELSE...
>> WE COULD HAVE KEPT IT BETWEEN
ME AND YOU.
>> JEREMY, COP ON NOW.
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN LIKE THAT IN
THIS GAME.
>> WHY NOT?
>> IT JUST DOESN'T.
IF I SAY, JEREMY, I GOT AN IDOL,
FIRST THING IN HIS HEAD, LET'S
PUT HIS NAME DOWN.
>> NOT IF WE'RE IN AN ALLIANCE.
>> NO.
>> BUT IT'S MORE THAN TWO
PEOPLE.
>> WE COULD HAVE TWO PEOPLE
ALIGNED AND HAVE A SUBALLIANCE
WITH EVERYBODY ELSE.
WE COULD HAVE DONE THAT.
>> SUBALLIANCE.
OKAY.
>> WE COULD HAVE DONE THAT,
KEITH.
>> THAT'S A NEW ONE ON ME.
>> IT'S NOT A NEW ONE IN
"SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: KEITH ONE OF THE
THINGS JEREMY SEEMS TO BE
SAYING, WHEN YOU'RE IN AN
ALLIANCE WITH SOMEBODY, YOU
DON'T BETRAY THEM.
>> I DON'T RECALL THIS BETRAYAL.
>> WELL, YOU STARTED PITTING
PEOPLE AGAINST JEREMY.
EVERYBODY WENT, WHOA.
>> THAT WASN'T THE WAY IT WAS
MEANT TO BE.
>> IT WASN'T LIKE, I THINK
JEREMY HAS AN IDOL, IT WAS LIKE,
"I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING, JEREMY
GOT THAT IDOL."
>> Jeff: SO DREW, WHAT DOES
THIS TRIBE NEED TO DO TONIGHT
WITH THE VOTE?
>> WELL, EVERYBODY HAD THEIR OWN
OPINION AT CAMP AND WHAT THE
RIGHT THING TO DO WAS.
I HEARD KEITH'S NAME.
I HEARD JULIE'S NAME.
YOU KNOW, SO IT'S JUST LIKE, I
WANT TO STRENGTHEN THE TEAM.
I WANT TO GET ANY BAD ENERGY OUT
AND ROLL FORWARD.
>> Jeff: KELLY, DO YOU AGREE
WITH THAT, YOU NEED TO GET RID
OF BAD ENERGY?
>> YEAH, BUT WHO IS THE BAD SEED
IN THIS BUNCH.
MAYBE WE DON'T ALL AGREE ON
THAT.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, WHAT DO YOU
THINK THE TRIBE NEEDS TO DO
TONIGHT?
>> I THINK THIS IS GOING TO BE A
REALLY CRITICAL VOTE.
AT ONE POINT TODAY DREW WAS
ACCUSING THE GIRLS WANTING TO
GET THE GUYS OUT.
I WAS LIKE WHAT?
>> Jeff: HOW WOULD THE GIRLS
TAKE OUT THE GUYS?
THERE'S ONLY FOUR.
>> THAT'S THE THING, JEFF, NONE
OF THE GIRLS APPROACHED ME AND
ASKED ME WHAT I THOUGHT WAS A
GOOD VOTE.
>> BECAUSE YOU FREAKED OUT THE
SECOND WE GOT BACK THE CAMP.
YOU CAN'T WANT TO TALK TO ME,
AND THEN I HEARD MY NAME GOING
AROUND, SO OBVIOUSLY YOU MAYBE
HAVE SOMETHING AGAINST ME.
>> JEFF, I THOUGHT WE WERE ALL
ON ONE PAGE, AND EVERYBODY SEEMS
TO BE SCATTERBRAINED BECAUSE
IT'S SCARY BECAUSE A FEW STRAY
VOTES CAN CHANGE EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: JON, WHAT DO YOU
THINK THE TRIBE NEEDS TO DO?
>> THERE WERE SO MANY DIFFERENT
STRATEGIES THAT WERE GOING ON, I
NEVER REALLY GOT A FULL GRASP OF
ANY OF THEM.
>> Jeff: THAT CANNOT BE
COMFORTING.
>> IT'S NOT AT ALL, ABSOLUTELY
NOT, BECAUSE I HONESTLY AM SO
CONFUSED WHAT NAME I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE WRITING DOWN RIGHT NOW.
>> JEFF, WE'RE A HOT MESS.
>> Jeff: AND IT'S ABOUT TO GET
A WHOLE LOT MESSIER BECAUSE IT'S
TIME TO VOTE.
DREW, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE JULIE.
KELLEY.
DREW.
KEITH.
THAT'S ONE VOTE JULIE.
ONE VOTE KELLY, ONE VOTE DREW.
ONE VOTE KEITH.
JULIE.
TWO VETS JULIE.
DREW.
TWO VOTES JULIE, TWO VOTES DREW,
ONE VOTE KELLEY, ONE VOTE KEITH.
DREW.
THAT'S THREE VOTES DREW, TWO
VOTES JULIE, ONE VOTE KELLEY,
ONE VOTE KEITH.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OR
"SURVIVOR" BLOOD VERSUS WATER,
DREW.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
GOOD PLAY.
>> Jeff: DREW, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> BUT.
>> Jeff: WELL, FOR A FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, THERE WAS A LOT
OF INFORMATION REVEALED.
FOUR PEOPLE GOT VOTES AND A
BLINDSIDE.
THE ONLY QUESTION: WAS IT A
BRILLIANT TRIBAL OR ABSOLUTE
CHAOS?
TIME WILL TELL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK THE CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> IF YOU OR THE GUYS SAID IT TO
ME, I WOULD HAVE BEEN ON BOARD
WITH IT.
>> IT'S JON VERSUS HUNAHPU.
>> YOU'RE EITHER WITH ME OR
AGAINST ME, AND IF YOU'RE NOT,
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> Jeff: BUT NOT FOR LONG.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
>> I KNEW IT.
>> SON OF A...
>> I KNEW ALL ALONG THOSE GIRLS
WANTED ME OUT OF.
THERE I'M OBVIOUSLY A PHYSICAL
AND SOCIAL THREAT TO THEM.
CONGRATS TO THEM.
THEY DID A GREAT JOB BY GETTING
ME OUT.
IN THE LONG RUN I WOULD HAVE
BEAT THEM.
I WISH I HAD BEEN MORE CHILL AND
ROLLED WITH THE GIRLS RATHER
THAN GONE AGAINST THEM RIGHT
AWAY BECAUSE IT TURNED OUT TO
BITE ME IN MY BUTT.