>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> CONGRATULATIONS, YOU ARE
MERGED!
>> Jeff: AFTER BLOOD AND WATER
MERGED, THERE WERE TWO BATTLING
ALLIANCES.
ONE LED BY JEREMY.
>> WE GOT ME, NAT, JULIE.
BAYLOR, AND YOU.
>> Jeff: THE OTHER ALLIANCE
LED BY JOSH.
>> IT'S ME AND REED, ALEC, WES,
AND PETE.
>> Jeff: BOTH WERE FIGHTING
FOR JON AND JACLYN.
>> FOR THE THIRD TRIBAL IN A ROW
WE FIND OURSELVES IN THE MIDDLE.
THIS IS A BIG DECISION.
>> KNOW.
>> Jeff: BUT IT WAS JOSH WHO
CONVINCED THEM TO JOIN HIS
ALLIANCE AND BLINDSIDE JEREMY.
>> WJEREMY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GOING TO
BE VOTING JEREMY OUT TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: FORTUNATELY FOR
JEREMY, JULIE MADE A SHOCKING
DECISION.
YOU'RE QUITTING THE GAME.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THROWING A WRENCH
INTO JOSH'S PLAN TO TAKE OUT
JEREMY AND LEAVING THE GAME UP
IN THE AIR.
SOMEBODY MAYBE JUST GOT A
MILLION-DOLLAR BREAK.
>> JEREMY IS ON BORROWED TIME
NOW, AND I DON'T THINK HE EVEN
REALIZED.
>> Jeff: 11 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M SO PISSED THAT
JULIE QUIT THAT WAY.
I JUST-- I WOKE UP, LIKE, GOING,
"ARE YOU SERIOUS?"
YOU DON'T QUIT!
BECAUSE JULIE QUIT, WE DIDN'T
HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL, AND IT
REALLY THREW A WRINKLE IN THE
PLAN.
I MEAN, I THINK FOR EVERYBODY.
MY ALLIANCE HAS THEIR PLAN TO
VOTE JOSH OUT.
WE'RE READY TO GO.
BUT WE CAN'T DO THAT UNTIL WE
GET TO A TRIBAL.
>> THIS IS THE PART OF THE GAME
WHERE IT'S LIKE, I KNOW I'M
PLAYING THE GAME, BUT I DON'T
KNOW IF WE'RE JUST BEING
DECEITFUL.
YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE WE'RE JUST GOING AROUND
TROUNCING JEREMY, WE GOT HIM,
TROUNCING MISSY AND BAYLOR, WE
GOT HIM, AND THEN BLINDSIDING
PEOPLE.
>> OH, WELL.
>> WE DIDN'T HAVE A TRIBAL LAST
NIGHT.
SO NOBODY KNOWS EXACTLY WHERE
JACLYN AND I STAND RIGHT NOW.
THEY THINK I'M SOLLOID THAT
SIDE, I'M SOLLOID THAT SIDE.
BUT THE FACT IS WE DECIDED ON
TAKING OUT JEREMY.
THIS MOVE IS A BIG MOVE.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> I MEAN, JEREMY IS THE LEADER
OF THE PACK.
AND TO TAKE HIM OUT THIS EARLY--
>> WELL, THINK ABOUT IT.
JOSH IS THE LEADER OF THE OTHER
PACK.
>> THAT'S WHY I THINK IT'S SO
GOOD RIGHT NOW THAT PEOPLE ARE
ASKING HOW DO WE WORK WHO JON
AND JACLYN, INSTEAD OF SAYING,
"HEY, GET JON AND JACLYN OUT."
>> YEAH, SO WE'RE FINE.
>> JEREMY IS GOING TO BE GOING
HOME VERY, VERY SOON.
ORIGINALLY WE TOLD HIM WE WERE
DOWN WITH VOTING OUT JOSH SO I
DON'T THINK HE HAS ANY CLUE
WHATSOEVER THAT JACLYN AND I
HAVE FLIPPED, BUT ULTIMATELY, I
DO NEED TO CONSIDER WHAT MY BEST
PATH IS, AND MY BEST PATH RIGHT
NOW DOES NOT INCLUDE JEREMY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE IS
IT.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING TO
DIVIDE INTO TWO TEAMS.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL RACE TO LOAD
HEAVY PUZZLE PIECES ON TO A
CART.
YOU'LL THEN PUSH THAT CART TO
THE BASE OF A TOWER, WHERE YOU
WILL USE THOSE PIECES TO BUILD A
TEMPLE.
ONCE THE TEMPLE IS BUILT, ONE
PERSON WILL RACE TO THE TOP OF
THE TEMPLE TO UNLOCK A STATUE.
YOU'LL THEN WORK TOGETHER TO
HOIST THE STATUE TO THE TOP
RAISING YOUR TRIBE FLAG.
FIRST TEAM TO RAISE THEIR FLAG
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>>
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: IT'S A NICE ONE.
IT IS A "SURVIVOR-"STYLE TACO
BAR.
>> OH!
>> MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: CHICKEN.
STEAK.
PORK.
>> WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS
ONE.
>>
>> Jeff: VEGETARIAN.
WASH IT DOWN, BEER.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: ICED TEA.
AND MARGARITAS.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'RE
GOING TO DO A SCHOOL YARD PICK
TO FIGURE OUT OUR TEAMS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR TWO
TEAMS.
IT IS KEITH, NATALIE, REED,
JEREMY AND WES TAKING ON JON,
ALEC, BAYLOR, JOSH, AND JACLYN.
MISSY WAS NOT PICKED, HAS NO
SHOT AT THE REWARD.
HERE WE GO FOR A BIG REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THESE ARE VERY HEAVY PIECES.
YOU WILL HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER.
THE QUESTION IS HOW MANY DO YOU
PUT ON EACH LOAD BECAUSE YOU'VE
STILL GOT TO GET THAT CART ALL
THE WAY TO THE END AND THAT
WON'T BE EASY.
YELLOW WITH FOUR.
YELLOW GOING TO GO FOR FIVE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, GO!
>> Jeff: YELLOW HEADING OUT.
>> DIG, DIG, DIG, DIG!
>> Jeff: YELLOW WITH A BIT OF
A LEAD.
BLUE GOT ONE VERY WOBBLY PIECE.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE SOMEBODY'S
HEAD FACE-OFF IT FALLS.
>> LIFT UP.
PUSH UP WHILE YOU'RE DOING IT.
>> Jeff: GOTTA GET TO THE END.
THERE YOU GO.
UNLOAD NOW, UNLOAD.
BLUE DOING A NICE JOB OF WORKING
TOGETHER.
EVERYBODY DIGGING.
>> PUSH!
>> Jeff: BLUE AT THE END.
START UNLODING.
AFTER 19 DAYS, THESE PIECES ARE
VERY HEAVY.
YELLOW CAN START HEADING BACK.
NATALIE, REED, KEITH, JEREMY,
WES, WORKING HARD IT FOR THOSE
TACOS.
>> LET'S GO!
>> BLUE NOW HEADING BACK.
LET'S DO IT, GO!
>> GO, GO, GO.
YELLOW LODING MORE UP.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE BIGGEST
REWARDS SO FAR THIS SEASON.
EVERYBODY CAN TASTE IT.
BLUE SLOWING DOWN.
JON AND ALEC TRYING TO PICK UP
SOME TIME.
GREAT TEAM WORK BY YELLOW
WORKING TOGETHER VERY WELL.
THEY'VE HAD THE LEAD FROM THE
BEGINNING.
CAN BLUE PICK IT UP?
YELLOW WITH THEIR LAST FEW
PIECES.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, PUSH!
>> Jeff: YELLOW HEADING OUT,
ONCE AGAIN FATHER AND SON
WORKING TOGETHER.
>> PUSH HARD HERE.
HERE WE GO!
>> Jeff: BLUE TRYING TO PICK
UP SOME TIME.
THERE'S A LOT OF WEIGHT ON THIS
CART.
>> COME ON!
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
>> Jeff: YOU GOT IT!
UNLOAD YELLOW.
YELLOW CAN START BUILDING YOUR
TEMPLE.
>> THAT ONE FIRST.
>> LAST ONE, GUYS.
>> Jeff: BLUE WITH THE LAST
PIECE.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: YOU CANNOT GIVE UP ON
YOURSELF IN THIS CHALLENGE.
IT'S TOO BIG A REWARD.
BLUE IS VERY CLOSE.
>> GO!
PUSH!
>> Jeff: THEY'RE THERE!
YOU'RE GOING TO BUILD A TEMPLE
NOW WITH ALL OF THESE PIECES.
YELLOW WITH A NICE EARLY LEAD TO
BUILDING THIS TEMPLE.
BLUE TEAM HAS THEIR FIRST PIECES
TOGETHER.
YELLOW WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> LET'S GO, GET THAT CORNER!
>> Jeff: BLUE HAS A LOT OF
TIME TO MAKE UP.
THEY ARE MOVING QUICKLY ON THIS
PUZZLE.
EVERYBODY GIVING EVERYTHING THEY
HAVE.
>> COME ON!
>> GO TO YOU!
>> Jeff: EVERY SECOND IS GOING
TO COUNT IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> GUYS I'M GOING TO RUN UP,
OKAY?
>> Jeff: YELLOW GETTING VERY
CLOSE TO FINISHING.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: CAN BLUE PICK IT UP?
>> DON'T GIVE UP!
>> Jeff: YELLOW WITH THE LAST
PIECE.
THEIR TEMPLE'S DONE.
NATALIE HEADS UP TO THE TOP FOR
YELLOW.
THAT'S IT.
START HOISTING IT.
THIS COULD BE IT.
BLUE TEAM FIGHTING TO GET BACK
IN THIS.
BUT IT'S TOO LATE.
WIN REWARD!
>> Jeff: KEITH, REED, JEREMY,
NATALIE, WES, HUGE REWARD.
SMILES ON EVERYBODY'S FACE.
ALL RIGHT, BIG DECISION TO MAKE
FROM THE WINNING TEAM.
BEFORE YOU ENJOY YOUR REWARD,
YOU'RE SENDING ONE PERSON TO
EXILE ISLAND.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> LET'S SEND SOMEBODY WHO
HASN'T BEEN.
>> I FEEL BAD ABOUT SENDING
MISSY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, JON OR ALEC?
>> Jeff: WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> WE'RE GOING TO SEND JON.
>> Jeff: GOING TO SEND JON.
WHY JON?
>> WELL, JON'S A BIG GUY.
>> WE FELT LIKE HE CAN MAKE IT
ON HIS OWN.
>> Jeff: SO, JON, THIS IS
ACTUALLY A COMPLIMENT.
>> APPARENTLY.
I'LL TAKE THE COMPLIMENT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE'S A
MAP.
GRAB IT, HEAD OUT.
>> ENJOY YOUR MEAL.
THINK ABOUT ME WHILE YOU'RE
TASTING IT.
>> Jeff: JON WILL RETURN IN
TIME FOR THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT, KEITH, JEREMY, REED,
NATALIE, WES, GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD OUT.
ENJOY YOUR AFTERNOON.
"SURVIVOR-"STYLE TACO BAR.
BAYLOR, JABLIN, ALEC, JOSH, AND
MISSY, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> ARE KIDDING ME.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> YOU HAVE MARGARITAS.
YOU HAVE CHIPS.
YOU HAVE TACOS.
YOU HAVE BEER.
>> CHEERS, GUYS.
>> TO THE ""W"."
>> WE WON THE AWARD AND IT WAS
AMAZING.
WE GOT TO COME TO THE
"SURVIVOR-"STYLE TACO BAR.
I FEEL REALLY BAD BECAUSE JOSH
HAS BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS FROM
THE GET-GO.
WE HAVE AN ECLECTIC MIX OF
PEOPLE FROM TWO DIFFERENT
ALLIANCES TOGETHER WHO DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING TO TALK ABOUT
NECESSARILY AND WE'RE ALL
JUSTICE TRYING TO KEEP THINGS
CALM AND KEEP THE HOMEOSTASIS.
>> WHO WANTS THE CHEESE CASE DEE
AS.
>> ARE WE SUPPOSED TO BE TALK
STRATEGY LIKE OTHER PEOPLE DO ON
REWARDS?
WE'RE JUST EATING.
THERE'S NO ALLIANCE HERE.
IT'S JEREMY AND ME ON ONE SIDE,
AND REED, KEITH, AND WES ON THE
OTHER SIDE.
YOU KNOW, IF WE HAD MISSY OR WE
HAD JON OVER HERE WE WOULD BE
STRATEGIZING THE ENTIRE TIME.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU ALL,
PUT LAST NIGHT, JULIE WAS KIND
OF MY PICK, AND IT COMES UP SHE
QUITS.
BUT IF THEY SAID JULIE IS GONE
BUT YOU ALL ARE STILL GOING,
MAN, I HAD NO IDEA AFTER THAT.
>> IF HE WOULD HAVE SAID STILL
GOING TO TRIBAL, I WOULD HAVE
BEEN SCREWED.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT HIM, BUT I
DIDN'T KNOW--
>> KEITH COMES OUT AND SAYS, "IF
WE HAD TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT
YESTERDAY, I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE
WOULD HAVE DONE.
WE WERE ALL UP IN THE AIR."
AND HE'S TELLING ME THIS.
AND I'M LOOK AT HIM LIKE, COME
ON, I KNOW YOU GUYS WERE
TARGETING ME.
GET OUT OF HERE.
IT TELLS ME KEITH IS AT LEAST
TRYING TO PLAY THE GAME, BUT I
DON'T THINK HE'S VERY GOOD AT
IT.
>> I WANT THREE OR FOUR HARD
TALK ORGANIZATION DOUBLE CHEESE,
DOUBLE MEAT.
>> TAKE IT EASY.
SLOW AND STEADY.
>> WINS THE RACE, YEAH.
MY DAD SAID SLOW DOWN, ENJOY IT,
AND, OF COURSE, I DIDN'T AT ALL,
AND I'M SCARFING DOWN BURRITOS,
QUESEDAS, MARGARITAS, AND BEER.
I JUST WISH I HAD THE WILL POWER
TO CONTROL MYSELF.
>> YOUR DOUBLE MEAT.
>> OH, YEAH!
>> TWO MORE AND HE'S GOING TO BE
SICK.
TWO MORE OF THOSE BABIES.
>> LIKE I'M REALLY WORRIED ABOUT
THAT.
IT WAS ALL FUN AND GIMUNTIL I
FELT LIKE CRAP.
( BURPS )
ALL RIGHT.
>> AS LONG AS YOU KEEP BURPING,
I GUESS YOU'RE OKAY.
WESLEY IS A GOOD KID.
HE AIN'T BEEN IN JAIL YET, YOU
KNOW, BUT HE DOES MAKE SOME
MISTAKES.
I CAN JUST GIVE HIM MY WORDS OF
WISDOM IS ABOUT ALL I CAN DO.
>> UH-OH.
>> WANDERING OFF.
>> THAT'S MY BOY OVERLODING OVER
THERE.
>> IT WILL PASS, MAN, JUST
BREATHE.
( BURPS )
>> OH!
>> WHO THE HECK RAISED HIM?
I DON'T-- HIS MAMMA?
I DON'T KNOW.
GOSH DARN.
>> OH!
>> THE SNAILS ARE PRETTY.
>> IT WILL BE PLENTY FOR ALL OF
US.
WELL, THE REWARD CHALLENGE,
NEEDLESS TO SAY, WE LOST.
AND, MAN, IT WAS FRUSTRATING.
BUT, HONESTLY, THIS COULDN'T
HAVE GONE BETTER AS FAR AS THE
PEOPLE I NEEDED TO BE TALKING TO
AND THE PEOPLE I NEEDED TO BE
BONDING WITH, SO I'M GOING TO
PUT MY LITTLE FEELERS OUT THERE
ONE MORE TIME WITH BAYLOR TO TRY
TO GET THE TARGET OFF MY BACK.
CAN I BE HONEST?
>> YEAH, OF COURSE,.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU OWE ME AT
LEAST ONE VOTE TO NOT VOTE FOR
ME.
I LITERALLY PUSHED FOR YOU EVERY
SINGLE TIME TO TAKE YOU OFF THE
CHOPPING BLOCK, AND LITERALLY
SAVED YOU ONCE.
IF YOUR ALLIANCE IS ALL GONNA
VOTE REED OR MYSELF, IF YOU
WOULD NOT VOTE THAT.
JUST OUT OF RESPECT BECAUSE I
FEEL LIKE I STUCK MY NECK OUT
FOR YOU A COUPLE OF TIMES.
>> IT WAS UNCOMFORTABLE WHEN
JOSH CAME UP TO ME AND SAID,
"YOU OWE ME."
I ALMOST FEEL LIKE I'M BEING,
LIKE, BLACKMAILED A LITTLE BIT.
TO ME, THAT JUST DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE A GUY WHO COMES FROM A
CHRISTIAN FAMILY AND A PASTOR
FOR A DAD.
I MEAN, I WAS TAUGHT THAT YOU
SHOULD GIVE A GIFT WITHOUT
EXPECTING ANYTHING IN RETURN,
SOYY FEEL LIKE I DON'T OWE HIM
ANYTHING.
THE THING THAT'S BEEN TOSSED
AROUND IN MY PLAYING FIELD IN MY
EARS, PEOPLE SAY JOSH USED YOU
AND DRUG YOU LONG SO HE COULD
CONTINUE USING YOU FOR A VOTE.
>> I KNOW.
AND I KNOW THAT'S PROBABLY WHAT
YOUR MOM HAS BEEN SAYING.
I WAS TRYING TO SOLIDIFY HER AND
MISSY'S VOTES FOR THE COUPLES
JUST TO GIVE US A COUPLE OF MORE
NUMBERS, BUT MISSY IS KIND OF
CONTROLLING BAYLOR RIGHT NOW.
AND I DON'T THINK THEY'RE GOING
TO VOTE WITH THE COUPLES SO AT
THIS POINT, I'M PRETTY FED UP
WITH BAYLOR.
I JUST A MINUTE AGO WAS TALKING
TO HER AND I WAS LIKE, "HERE'S
THE DEAL, BAYLOR.
I DID SAVE YOU."
AND I WAS LIKE, "IT WOULD BE
GREAT IF YOU JUST GAVE ME ONE
VOTE AT ONE POINT."
NOT THAT IT'S GOING TO HELP
ANYTHING.
>> RIGHT.
>> FACT.
>> I DON'T MIND SEEING MY NAME.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GO OUT, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> RIGHT.
>> I REALLY AM HOPING JON AND
JACLYN ARE BEING TRUTHFUL BUT
ALL I CAN DO RIGHT NOW IS HOPE
THEY ARE AND TRY AND KEEP THAT
RELATIONSHIP GOING.
>> EXILE ISLAND IS EXTREMELY
DESOLATE.
AND BEING OUT HERE BY MYSELF
SUCKS.
I'M LONELY.
I MISS JACLYN.
I DO FEEL LIKE WITH JACLYN IN MY
GAME, SHE'S, OBVIOUSLY, BEEN
HELPING ME MAKE ALL THE
DECISIONS.
WITH ME AWAY, IT GIVES JACLYN
HER CHANCE TO BUILD THOSE
RELATIONSHIPS UP SO THAT SHE'S
NOT JUST SEEN AS, LIKE THE
TAGALONG.
"HERE AT EXILE, LACK OF WATER IS
A DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD.
IT CAN QUENCH YOUR THIRST FOR
POWER.
FOR MOTHER NATURE'S COOPERATION
YOU MUST CHOOSE THE PROPER
HOUR."
I OPEN UP THE CLUE, AND MY REERS
IMMEDIATELY PERKED.
IT'S A CLUE TO A NEW IDOL THAT'S
HERE ON EXILE INSTEAD OF BACK AT
OUR CAMP.
AND THIS IS HUGE.
IT SAID, "LACK OF WATER SAY
DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD."
SO I'M THINKING I HAVE TO GO
SEARCHING WHILE THE TIDE IS LOW
AND THE SWORD KIND OF LOOKS LIKE
A PENINSULA, AND I LOOK AND
THERE'S THIS BIG PENINSULA
STICKING OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF
EXILE ISLAND.
SO I'M THINKING IT'S GOT TO BE
OVER THERE.
AS I MAKE MY WAY AROUND, THERE'S
A BILLION ROCKS HERE.
I'M LOOKING UNDER ALL OF THEM.
BUT I CAN'T FIEND AN IDOL.
THE TIDE WAS COMING UP.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M GOING TO GET
ANOTHER CHANCE TO LOOK FOR IT.
I WAS LIKE, I NEED TO FIND IT
RIGHT NOW.
THE NEXT LOGICAL PLACE THAT IT
WOULD BE IS UP ON THIS BIG
PILLAR RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE THAT
I HAVEN'T CLIMBED YET.
ROCK.
OH, YES!
WOO-EEE!
FOUND ME A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
OH, THANK YOU, GOD.
SHE IS A BEAUTY.
THAT'S A GAME CHANGER.
THEN IT'S EXCITING TO HAVE THAT
KIND OF POWER IN THE GAME
BECAUSE NOW WHATEVER I WANT TO
HAPPEN REALLY IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
THERE'S MY IDOL!
I KEPT WAKING UP TO... OH, MAN.
>> I HAVEN'T DONE THAT YET.
I WISHED I HAD BURPED AND FARTS.
IF I DID, I WOULD MAKE SURE SHE
SMELLED THEM.
>> WES AND ALEC AND KEITH,
THEY'RE JUST RUDE,UN.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN TRYING TO HIDE
IT, AND THEY'RE LAUGHING.
IT.
>> YOU AND JON ARE THE ONLY
GENTLEMEN.
THE REST OF THEM, THEY'RE A
BUNCH OF PIGS
>> THEY'RE SO RUDE.
IT'S CRAZY.
I MEAN, AS A FIREFIGHTER, WE ACT
LIKE THAT AT THE FIREHOUSE
SOMETIMES,UN WHAT I MEAN?
BUT AS SOON AS A WOMAN COMES
WILL IN THE ROOM, YOU SHUT IT
DOWN.
EVERYONE'S ON THEIR BEST
BEHAVIOR BECAUSE THAT'S HOW
YOUABT AROUND WOMEN.
BUT THESE GUYS, THEATRE FIRST
ONES TO EAT, LIKE JUMPING IN
FRONT OF THE GIRLS.
I'M LIKE WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING?
HAVE SOME MANNERS.
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> IT'S TRASH.
>> WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO WITH
IT.
>> THROW IT AWAY IN THE WATER.
>> DUDE.
ALREADY.
>> WHAT?
>> NOTHING.
I'M DOWN.
I FEEL LIKE A SLAVE, BUT I'M
DOWN.
>> YOU FEEL LIKE A SLAVE?
YOU WANT SOME FISH?
I MEAN, THIS AIN'T NO CHARITY
NOW?
>> ALEC TREATS ME LIKE I'M HIS
BABY SISTER WHO HE WANTS TO BUG,
AND THAT'S BEEN THE CASE SINCE
DAY ONE.
SO I'M KIND OF OVER IT.
>> HE'S LIKE THAT TO ALL THE
WOMEN.
HE'S RUDE TO ME, TOO.
JUST ROLL IT OFF YOUR BACK.
>> I'M TRYING BUT IT'S JUST
OBNOXIOUS.
MOI MOM IS LIKE, "JUST, LET IT
GO."
UNFORTUNATELY, I GET BUGGED
EASILY.
>> COME ON, BAYLOR.
WE'LL COME AND GET SOME WOOD PUP
AIN'T DONE NOTHING BUT LAY THERE
ALL DAY.
AT LEAST CHECK A PULSE EVERY NOW
AND THEN.
>> I HAVE TO GET WOOD.
>> ARE WE ON BREAK?
IT'S HARD TO GET GOOD HELP.
>> OKAY, REPORTING TO FOR DUTY.
>> IF YOU WERE MY KID YOU WOULD
HAVE GOT WOOPED 10 TIMES TODAY.
>> IT'S THE MOST CHAUVINISTIC
GROUP I HAVE MET.
I HAVE SEEN RUDE PEOPLE BEFORE
BUT THIS IS THE WORST.
>> GIRLS, KEEP THIS FIRE GOING.
NATALIE WILL DO IT.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY WILL.
>> DID YOU HEAR WHAT HE SAID?
>> THAT WAS AN ANNOYING COMMENT.
>> LIKE, SHOULDN'T THEY TRY TO
BE NICE TO ME?
LIKE, THEY NEED MY VOTE, AND
WHATEVER I REALLY WANT, JON WILL
DO.
SO-- THE GUYS ON THIS TRIBE ARE
REALLY ARROGANT AND RUDE.
I ALREADY KNEW THAT, BUT, LIKE,
AFTER JON LEFT, OH, MY GOSH, I
SAW SUCH A DIFFERENCE IN THE WAY
THEY TREATED ME.
AND I'M JUST LIKE, SCREW YOU,
GUYS.
WITHOUT ME AND JON'S VOTE, YOU
DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
THEY'RE SO DUMB.
>> AND ALSO THE FACT THAT-- ALL
YOU DO IS--
>> JON CAN VOTE WITH THEM, BUT
I'M NOT.
NO WAY.
>> AGAIN, WE CAN'T LET JEREMY
WIN.
>> NO, THAT'S TRUE.
WE STILL NEED TO TOUCH BASE WITH
JON.
>> ALTHOUGH, WE ALREADY GOT OUR
PLAN.
HE WANTS TO DO, AND IT'S TIME TO
DO IT WHO ELSE YOU GOTTA TOUCH
BASE WITH?
>> I WOULD THINK JACLYN.
>> YEAH, NO, SHE'S GOING TO BE
DOWN.
SHE'S GOING TO VOTE WITH JON.
>> SHE'S BEEN TALKING TO BAYLOR
THIS WHOLE TIME.
NO TELLING WHAT IN THE HECK--
>> I'M TELLING YOU, JON'S RIDING
WITH THE BOYS.
I'M TELL YOU.
I FEEL AS COMFORTABLEAISE
PROBABLY COULD RIGHT NOW BECAUSE
JON IS A SMART DUDE.
HE KNOWS THAT JEREMY IS A
THREAT, AND HE TRUSTS ME, AND
THAT'S BIG DISPP I KNOW THAT
JACLYN'S GOING TO DO WHATEVER
JON SAYS.
SO THIS ALLIANCE IS STICKING
TOGETHER AND AS LONG AS JEREMY
DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY, WE'RE
GOING TO VOTE HIM OUT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WE'LL NOW BRING IN JON RETURNING
FROM EXILE ISLAND.
( APPLAUSE )
>> HI.
>> HI, BABY.
>> I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
KEITH, I WILL TAKE BACK THE
NECKLACE.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING TO HELP
ME.
>> I WANT TO KEEP IT.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO SEE WHAT
KIND OF IMPACT 21 DAYS HAS HAD
ON AREA MIND.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU A SERIES
OF SYMBOLS.
YOU'RE GOING TO USE YOUR CUBE TO
REPEAT THEM BACK TO ME.
GET IT RIGHT, YOU STAY ALIVE.
GET IT WRONG, YOU'RE OUT.
THE LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING
WINS IMMUNITY.
SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
BIG STAKES.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FIRST ROUND.
STATUE.
>> STATUE.
>> Jeff: SUN.
SKULL.
AXE.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY FIND THE
FIRST ICON.
REVEAL IT.
EVERYBODY HAS STATUE.
EVERYBODY'S RIGHT.
NEXT ICON.
SEVEAL IT.
EVERYBODY SHOWS SUN EXCEPT JON.
HE HAS SKULL.
CORRECT ANSWER, SUN.
JON IS FIRST OUT.
JON, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
THAT IS PROBABLY INDICATIVE OF
TWO DAYS ON EXILE ISLAND ALL
ALONE.
NEXT ICON, REVEAL.
EVERYBODY SHOWS SKULL EXCEPT
REED WHO HAS TEMPLE.
IF HE'S RIGHT, HE WINS.
BUT INSTEAD, YOU'RE OUT.
CORRECT ANSWER IS SKULL.
REED IS OUT.
REED JOINS JON ON THE BENCH.
NEXT ICON, REVEAL.
EVERYBODY HAS AN AXE EXCEPT WES
AND ALEC, WHO ARE SHOWING MASK.
CORRECT ANSWER, AXE.
WES IS OUT.
ALEC IS OUT.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO SEVEN.
HERE WE GO.
NEXT ROUND.
AXE.
SKULL.
MASK.
>> TOMIA HAWK, SKULL...
>> Jeff: SUN.
>> TEMPLE.
AXE.
STATUE.
>> AXE, SKULL...
>> Jeff: FIRST ICON, EVERYBODY
REVEAL.
EVERYBODY HAS AXE EXCEPT FOR
NATALIE WHO HAS SKULL.
IT WAS AXE.
NATALIE IS WRONG.
NATALIE IS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO SIX.
NEXT ICON.
REVEAL.
EVERYBODY SHOWS SKULL EXCEPT
BAYLOR WHO SHOWS SUN.
CORRECT ANSWER, SKULL.
BAYLOR IS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
NEXT ICON.
REVEAL.
EVERYBODY SHOWS MASK EXCEPT JACK
LEN.
JACLYN HAS SUN.
ARE YOU SECOND GUESSING, JACLYN?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: CORRECT ANSWER IS
MASK.
JACLYN IS WRONG.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS RIGHT.
WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
EVERYBODY FIND YOUR NEXT ICON
AND REVEAL.
VERY INTERESTING.
JOSH AND JEREMY BOTH SHOW SUN.
MISSY AND KEITH BOTH SHOW
TEMPLE.
CORRECT ANSWER IS SUN.
KEITH IS OUT, MISSY IS OUT.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO OUR FINAL
TWO, JOSH AND JEREMY.
>> COME ON, JOSH.
>> Jeff: BIG IMMUNITY ON THE
LINE.
NEXT ICON.
FIND IT AND REVEAL.
>> Jeff: JOSH SHOWS STATUE.
JEREMY SHOWS TEMPLE.
ONE OF SURIGHT, ONE IS WRONG.
CORRECT ANSWER IS TEMPLE.
JEREMY WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
>> GOOD JOB, MAN.
( APPLAUSE )
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
>> GOOD JOB, JEREMY.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, SAFE TONIGHT
AT THE VOTE, CANNOT BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME, GUARANTEED A ONE
IN 10 SHOT AT WINNING THE
MILLION BUCKS.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 21
DAYS IN A VERY TOUGH GAME,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
>> FREEZE FRAME!
>> CONGRATULATIONS!
AWESOME.
>> YOU MISSED YOU.
>> I HAVE THE IDOL.
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> I WON THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
TODAY, AND IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL
THING.
I KNOW THAT JOSH AND HIS GOONS
WERE COMING AFTER ME, SO IT'S
HUGE.
>> GOOD WORK TODAY, Y'ALL.
>> YEAH, YOU, TOO, MAN.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE OUR ALLIANCE
IS ALL SET WITH VOTING FOR JOSH.
THE TWO OF US HAVE BEEN BATTLING
EACH OTHER FOR CONTROL OF THE
GAME, BUT NOW IT'S ALL ABOUT JON
AND JACLYN AND I'M HOPING
THEY'RE ON MY SIDE.
BECAUSE IF NOT, I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO KEEP WEARING THIS
BEAUTIFUL THING, YOU KNOW, IN
ORDER TO STAY ALIVE.
>> WHO DO WE WANT IT TO BE?
>> I SAY BAYLOR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> YEAH.
>> HE DEFINITELY WANTS TO GET
BAYLOR OUT, KEITH DOES.
>> YOUR DAD WILL BE GOOD WITH
THAT?
>> 100%.
>> LET'S JUST DO IT.
BECAUSE AS LONG AS J. AND J. ARE
ON BOARD, IT WILL WORK EXACTLY
AS PLANNED.
RIGHT NOW THE PLAN IS TO VOTE
FOR BAYLOR TONIGHT.
I TRIED TO GET BAYLOR ON MY
SIDE, BUT SHE DIDN'T GO FOR IT.
SO SHE'S GOT TO GO.
BUT RIGHT NOW, I'M RELYING ON
JACLYN AND JON TO GO ON OUR SIDE
BECAUSE IF NOT, TODAY IS MY LAST
DAY OUT HERE.
>> HOW WAS EVERYTHING WHILE I
WAS GONE?
>> WELL, I DON'T LIKE THE GUYS
ANYMORE AT ALL.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD GO WITH
THEM.
>> WHY?
>> WELL, FOR ONE, THEY DON'T
TALK TO ME WHEN YOU'RE NOT HERE.
THEY DON'T EVEN REGARD ME.
AND JUST THINKING ABOUT IT IN
ALL THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGES, OUR
BIGGEST THREATS ARE THOSE GUYS.
I CAN'T WIN AGAINST THEM PUP ARE
GOING TO HAVE A TOUGH TIME.
WHY DON'T WE JUST VOTE THEM OUT
FIRST?
>> COMING BACK FROM EXILE, I HAD
INITIALLY THOUGHT THAT JACLYN
AND I WERE GOING TO BE ALIGNING
WITH JOSH AND THE GUYS.
BUT THEN JACLYN BROUGHT UP SOME
INTERESTING INFORMATION THAT
WHILE I WAS GONE, THE GUYS WERE
COMPLETELY IGNORING HER THE
WHOLE TIME AND MADE HER FEEL
LIKE CRAP.
I MEAN, THIS IS THE LOVE OF MY
LIFE TALKING.
HOWEVER, THIS IS A GAME.
AND IT CAN'T BE JUST ACTING ON
EMOTIONS.
>> WE HAVE A BETTER TIME BEATING
MISSY, NATALIE, BAYLOR, AND--
>> BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO BEAT
JEREMY IN THE FINAL THREE.
HE'S GOING TO WIN.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> HOW'S IT GOING.
>> HI.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> NOCT.
>> WHO'S GOING HOME TONIGHT?
>> THE PLAN RIGHT NOW IS TO VOTE
BAYLOR.
EVERYONE WANTS BAYLOR OUT.
BECAUSE SHE'S ANNOYING.
>> AND SHE'S NOT DOING ANYTHING.
>> I MISSED YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
>> I KNOW.
TWO DAYS.
THAT WAS SO BRUTAL.
ALL RIGHT, KIDS, I'M GOING TO
GO.
>> JON AND I HAVE TO DECIDE
WHICH WAY TO GO.
I THOUGHT THAT JON WAS GOING TO
HAVE MY BACK, BUT HE'S WORRIED
ABOUT TEAMING UP WITH JEREMY
BECAUSE HIS STORY WOULD WIN OVER
OUR STORY IN THE FINAL THREE.
SO JON'S THINKING REALLY FAR
AHEAD, WHICH IS STUPID.
BUT NOW I FEEL LIKE THERE'S ALL
THIS UP IN THE AIR WITH
EVERYTHING.
>> WHOSE TURN IS IT TO GO WHAT
ARE YOU ALL THINKING?
>> KEITH, ARE YOU BASICALLY
LIKE-- IS THAT WHERE YOU ARE?
>> NOT REALLY.
>> CAN'T YOU SWAY THEM, KEITH?
>> WELL--
>> HERE IT IS-- AND I HATE TO BE
BLUNT, BUT BAYLOR DON'T DO
( BLEEP ).
YOU KNOW THAT.
BAYLOR SLEEPS AND SHE GOES OVER
AND EATS.
I'VE BEEN HERE SIX DAYS AND I'VE
SEEN HER WITH ONE SCIENTIFIC
WOOD IN HER HANDS.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU.
AND WHAT GET ME, I SAY, "COME
ON, BAYLOR, "AND IF BAYLOR
SAYS,"I'M TIRED.
I WANT TO TAKE A NAP.
YOU JUMP IN AND YOU DO IT.
>> YOU PROTECT YOUR SON, TOO.
>> NOT LIKE, THAT THOUGH.
WESLEY-- LORLD, NO, I DON'T DO
THAT TO WESLEY.
I'M JUST-- I'M-- JUST THE FACTS,
MISSY.
>> I'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS
GUNNING FOR BAYLOR THING FOR A
WHILE NOW AND I GOT MY EAR BENT
ALREADY TODAY BY KEITH, "BAYLOR
DOESN'T DO ANYTHING."
IT DOESN'T FEEL GOOD EVER TO
HAVE YOUR CHILD PICKED ON.
I'M GOING TO BACK HER AND THAT'S
ALL THAT MATTERS.
>> WHAT DID KEITH SAY?
>> YOU.
>> HE TOLD YOU THAT?
TO MY FACE.
HE'S NOT REAL SMART.
>> I KNOW.
I NEED TO TALK TO JON.
>> YEAH, YOU DO.
I JUST FOUND OUT THAT KEITH SPIT
OUT MY NAME TO MY MOM, WHICH IS
STUPID.
YOU DON'T TELL THE MOM THAT
YOU'RE VOTING FOR THE DAUGHTER,
PERIOD.
BUT NOW, I'M, OBVIOUSLY, ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
I HAVE, LIKE, SICKENING
BUTTERFLIES IN MY STOMACH.
SO I KIND OF JUST HAVE TO BE
PREPARED AND HOPE THAT MY
ALLIANCE PULLS THROUGH.
>> COOL.
YEAH.
TONIGHT, JACLYN AND I HAVE TO
MAKE A VERY BIG DECISION.
AND THE SUCCESS WE'VE HAD SO FAR
HAS BEEN AS A RESULT OF JACLYN
AND I WORKING TOGETHER VERY
WELL.
BUT THIS TIME, JACLYN'S NOT ON
THE SAME PAGE AS I AM.
WE'RE GONNA VOTE JOSH.
>> HEY, WE'RE IN CONTROL OF THIS
GAME.
IF WE GET BAYLOR OUT, LET'S DO
IT.
>> YEAH.
>> I KNOW.
>> I DON'T TRUST JON.
HE'S SNEAKY.
>> TOMORROW IT'S GONNA BE VERY
CLEAR.
>> EITHER VERY CLEAR OR VERY
SHADY.
>> YEAH.
>> I WANT NOTHING TO DO WITH
THOSE GUYS.
BUT IT FEELS LIKE JON JUST
DOESN'T CARE.
I FEEL SO COMFORTABLE WITH MISSY
AND JEREMY.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
>> I THINK THAT'S A BIG MISTAKE.
>> AFTER TONIGHT, THERE'S GOING
TO BE A GOOD PORTION OF PEOPLE
MAD AT US, NO MATTER WHICH WAY
WE GO.
IT'S HARD BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO
WEIGH SO MANY DIFFERENT THINGS,
AND WE'RE STILL GOING BACK AND
FORTH.
HOPEFULLY WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT,
BUT NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
SOMEBODY'S NOT GOING TO BE
HAPPY.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, LET'S TALK
ABOUT TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
YOU ALWAYS WANTED IMMUNITY BUT
WAS THERE ANY ADDED PRESSURE
TODAY THAT YOU FELT I NEED IT?
THIS IS THE GOING TO BE A CRAZY
ONE.
>> LET ME TELL YOU, JEFF, TODAY,
IF I DIDN'T WIN THIS, PEOPLE
WERE WRITING MY NAME DOWN AND I
KNEW IT.
>> Jeff: JOSH, SAME QUESTION.
JEREMY CLEARLY THOUGHT I NEEDED
IT TONIGHT.
DID YOU FEEL THAT KIND OF
PRESSURE?
>> ABSOLUTE.
I KNEW MY NAME WAS BEING TOSSED
AROUND SO I KNEW I NEEDED IT FOR
TONIGHT'S VOTE.
>> Jeff: WES, ARE THE
ALLIANCES KNOWN?
>> I THINK THE ALLIANCES ARE
KNOWN.
I MEAN, ME, JOSH, REED, AND ALEC
TEAMED UP WITH DAD, AND I FELT
LIKE IT WAS KNOWN TO PEOPLE THAT
WE WERE WORKING TOGETHER TYPE.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, DOES THAT
LEAVE YOU NATALIE, MISSY,
BAYLOR, JACLYN AND JON TOGETHER?
>> IT COULD.
I'M NOT SURE.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, YOU'RE A PART
OF A LOVE PAIR.
WHERE DOES DOES THAT LEAVE AND
YOU JON IN TERMS OF ALLIANCES?
>> WELL, JON AND ME HAVE BEEN
APPROACHED BY BOTH SIDES SO THAT
KIND OF PUTS US IN THE MIDDLE OF
EVERYTHING, WHICH IS
INTERESTING.
>> Jeff: JON HOW IS THAT
POSSIBLE?
THERE HAVE BEEN MANY TRIBALS NOW
THAT YOU AND JACLYN HAVE BEEN
SORT OF THE SWING.
>> I CAN TELL YOU THAT'S THAT'S
NOT WHAT WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO
PUT OURSELVES IN.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE WE HAVE
SOMETHING PAINTED ON US THAT IS
LIKE LIKE, "TALK TO US, AND WE
MIGHT HELP YOU."
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HECK IT IS
BUT--
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, WHEN YOU SEE
THAT JON'S GETTING APPROACHED
BYE EVERYBODY, WHAT'S THE PLAY?
BECAUSE EVERYBODY'S PROBABLY GOT
A PRETTY GOOD PITCH.
>> IT'S SO WEIRD, BUT I FEEL
ALMOST PROTECTIVE OVER THE
ORIGINAL HUNAHPU.
AND JON IS SMIB FELT I COULD
TRUST SO YOU NEED TO PICK A SIDE
AND TRUST MOVINGED FOR.
THE FUNNY THING IS, THOSE GUYS
WERE CAMPAIGNING FOR JACLYN, BUT
WHEN JON IS NOT THERE, THE
BEHAVIOR SEEMS THEY DON'T EVEN
NEED JACLYN--
>> WHICH IS SO FRUSTRATING TO
ME.
EVERYONE GOES TO JON, AND THEN
WHEN HE WENT TO EXILE, NOBODY
REALLY CARED TO CAMPAIGN WITH
ME, AND THE SECOND HE GOT BACK
TODAY, IT WAS ALL ABOUT JON.
AND, YOU KNOW, ME AND JON TALK.
WE MAKE DECISION TOGETHER.
SO PEOPLE SHHH MAYBE BE SMARTER
ABOUT THAT.
>> Jeff: DO YOU NOT FEEL
RESPECTED OUT HERE?
>> MAYBE BY A FEW PEOPLE, YEAH,
I WOULD SAY THAT A LITTLE BIT.
>> I CAN LAY THIS OUT FOR YOU.
OKAY, SO I'M WATCHING A COUPLE
OF THESE YOUNGER GUYS PRETEND
LIKE THEY'RE IN A FRAT HOUSE.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO BE
TALKING ABOUT WES AND ALEC.
>> YOU GOT IT.
AND THEY LITERALLY BELCH, FART,
SPIT, THEY DON'T CARE IF THERE
ARE FEMALES THERE OR NOT.
>> BUT WE'RE NOT AT THE HILTON,
MISSY.
AND I HAVEN'T HEARD WESLEY FART,
OR SPIT.
BUT I'VE HAY LITTLE BIT OF GAS.
I'M SURE EVERYBODY ON THIS PANEL
HAS HAD GAS.
IT'S JUST A NORMAL BODY
FUNCTION.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR" AND STUFF
LIKE THAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET DIRTY.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET NORTHWEST.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET GAS.
>> Jeff: REED IT'S A
FASCINATING THING TO WATCH
TONIGHT BECAUSE PERCEPTION IS
REALITY TO THE PERCEIVER.
IF SOMEBODY BELIEVES THEY'RE
BEING DISRESPECTED, LIKE JACLYN,
ARE YOU THAT WAY TO THEM.
>> I THINK I'VE BEEN NOTHING BUT
RESPECTFUL TO THE WOMEN OUT
HERE.
BUT I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE I
MOMENT TO GO BACK TO WHEN
NATALIE PITCHED HER CASE TO JON
AND JACLYN, AND I THINK IT WOULD
BE JUST AS VALUABLE FOR US TO
GET A CHANCE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, REED, MAKE
YOUR CASE.
>> I JUST THINK YOU GUYS ARE
BOTH VERY POWERFUL, AND YOU'RE
STRONG TOGETHER.
YOU'RE BOTH THREATS IN
CHALLENGES.
SO IF YOU SIDE WITH A GROUP OF
SINGLES, WHAT'S TO SAY THEY
DON'T TURN RIGHT BACK AROUND OW
AND VOTE YOU GUYS OUT.
>> OKAY, WAIT, SO YOU'RE SAYING
YOU GUYS AREN'T GOING TO TURN
AROUND AND GET HIM OUT BECAUSE
JONL IS THE BIGGEST THREAT?
>> ABSOLUTE NOT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: JON, YOU'RE BEING
PITCHED FROM TWO GROUPS, A GROUP
OF FIVE AND A GROUP OF FOUR.
WOULD YOU RATHER YOU GUYS
WEREN'T THE LINCHPIN?
>> I THINK RIGHT NOW, I FEEL
LIKE IT'S POSITIVE BECAUSE I
FEEL LIKE JACLYN AND I ARE KIND
OF CONTROLLING OUR OWN FATE, BUT
THESE DECISIONS WE'RE MAKING,
THEY'RE GAME CHANGERS, AND THAT
CAN BE SCARY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
REED, YOU'RE UP.
>> SORRY YOU CAN'T HANDLE
HANGING OUT WITH THE BIG BOYS.
>> YOU'RE A STRONG PLAYER, BUT I
STOPPED TRUSTING YOU WHEN YOU
WROTE MY NAME DOWN THE FIRST
TRIBAL AND DIDN'T TELL ME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, BAYLOR.
JOSH.
BAYLOR.
TWO VOTES BAYLOR.
JOSH.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES JOSH, TWO
VOTES BAYLOR.
BAYLOR.
THREE VOTES BAYLOR.
JOSH.
THAT'S THREE VOTES JOSH.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES BAYLOR.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN, FOUR VOTES
BAIL OFOUR VOTES JOSH.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES BAYLOR.
WE'RE TIED.
FIVE VOTES JOSH, FIVE VOTES
BAYLOR.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
SEVENth PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JOSH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: JOSH, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> I'LL HAVE A CHEESEBURGER FOR
EVERYBODY.
>> Jeff: WELL, THE QUESTION
AFTER TONIGHT'S VOTE, IS THIS A
LINE IN THE SAND OR IS TOMORROW
A WHOLE NEW GAME?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": WITH JOSH GONE,
REED IS WILLING TO LIE, CHEAT,
AND STEAL TO STAY IN THE GAME.
>> DESPERATE TIMES CALL FOR
DESPERATE MEASURES.
>> Jeff: AND IT THROWS THE
CAMP INTO CHAOS.
>> KEITH HAS AN IDOL.
>> YOU KNOW KEITH HAS AN IDOL.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S ABOUT TO GET CRAZY.
>> I MEAN, THIS GAME IS ALL
ABOUT TRUST AND MAKING
ALLIANCES, AND I NEVER FULLY
TRUSTED THE ALLIANCE I HAD GOING
INTO TONIGHT.
I THINK IT JUST REVEALED JUST A
LITTLE TOO MUCH OF WHO I WAS OUT
HERE, AND THAT SENT ME PACKING.
SO I'M THANKFUL THAT I GOT THIS
FAR IN THIS GAME AND GOT THIS
EXPERIENCE.
IT'S BEEN AWESOME.