english from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
"The game has begun."
"This may be
your only night together."
"Help each other and learn
to make shelter and fire."
"At dawn, follow the path
on your map."
"Leave the flint and scraper
behind."
They come from all walks of life.
Oh my God!
As a couple, Jon and Jaclyn already have
experience of winning.
She is Miss Michigan 2013,
he played football
for the Michigan team.
Miss Michigan becomes a survivor!
Look at me!
- Our relationship is phenomenal.
- We are having fun.
But it goes beyond
the beautiful image that people have.
I don't want to be hated
- like a perfect little couple.
- Yeah.
Former professional baseball
player, John Rocker
created controversy 15 years ago.
I spent
the last 15 years
trying to say I'm not
that obnoxious rambunctious guy,
but the media loves to portray me as
a bigoted, homophobic racist.
It's a heavy label.
His longtime companion, Julie,
hope to provide him with the
necessary support to accomplish a perfect game
and go all the way.
I have a lot to prove.
We could say:
"Look at her, with her hair,
her tits and her boyfriend!"
But I am very independent,
I can take care of myself.
- There are a thousand crab holes.
- I see!
Here is one! Uh, hi!
Snakes don't live
in holes, right?
Baylor,
we need to start a fire.
Seriously, we're going to run out of light.
Oh my God!
Lord!
Mother and daughter, Missy and Baylor
know what adversity is.
He comes over here.
Missy's three divorces
pushed Baylor
to assume the maternal role
in this complicated relationship.
- Shit!
- They are five.
Divorces have brought us closer together.
What happens to me affects him,
and vice versa.
Absolutely.
The mother-daughter bond is incredible.
He is indestructible.
Nothing will stop us.
It's impossible.
Go on!
It did not work.
Cut a lock of your hair.
Brothers Drew and Alec,
from rural Florida,
have always had
a sibling rivalry.
Drew, the youngest, would love
to beat his brother in the game.
Drew and I have been fighting
pretty much since I was born.
I hope to prove to him
that I can beat him at this game.
I would love to see him fight.
- Honestly, I would love to.
- You'll be in the front row!
It was a team effort, right?
I was holding
the flint and the scraper, right?
I suppose.
Dad, take a break!
Don't hurt yourself yet!
A hard worker,
Dale has never known anything but the farm.
But growing up, her daughter Kelley
wanted to go her own way.
Of all the teams, we should
be the fastest at making fire!
Our relationship has had its ups
and downs for 10 years.
For 3 or 4 years,
we didn't speak to each other.
I think Survivor
will help us find each other.
We will share this
for the rest of our lives.
We're in bad shape!
Damn, a huge crab!
Grab it!
Old Survivor fans
and couple, Josh and Reed
are performing on Broadway, New York.
You got it!
Both think they can
survive 39 days in this jungle.
- Stir it up!
- Yeah!
We lost it!
We're both big fans.
- This guy, for Valentine's Day...
- Here we go!
...offers me flint!
I offered him flint!
- Go on!
- We are comfortable in the open air,
to sleep in the dirt,
and we are ready for it.
We'll eat you for dinner!
We did it!
They have abandoned the comfort
and safety of their universe.
For 39 days,
they will be on their own.
It's a bit upside down.
- A firefighter lighting a fire!
- Not bad not bad!
Val, the Boston police officer
and her firefighter husband Jeremy
have a form
of professional rivalry,
despite their mad love.
I've been trying to participate
in Survivor for 10 years.
I didn't bring her here,
leaving our girls at home...
- To lose.
- ...to lose.
We are both here
to win.
May the best profession win!
So we spend the night here?
Let's start by praying and we will advise.
Sri Lankan twins
Nadiya and Natalie
played aggressively in
The Amazing Race,
and they failed twice.
They now hope to
go all the way
of their greatest adventure
yet.
- We hope to finally win.
- The third is the good one!
In The Amazing Race,
we had everything we needed.
Remove the essential,
and you have Survivor
Sleepless nights, empty bellies...
Survivor will be much harder
than The Amazing Race.
Let him take it, Nadiya, relax.
- Shit, you suffocated him!
- But no!
Nadiya, he was taking!
Our bonds are stronger
than those of anyone here.
I guarantee it.
'Cause we were never apart
more than two weeks.
We need help!
I will light a fire before dark.
To keep bugs away.
Firefighters in Louisiana
and father and son, Keith and Wes
have the same love
of their job and the outdoors.
Wes, have you lost the scraper yet?
I gave you both.
But when Keith
is almost retired...
You're kidding?
...he's not ready
to hand over to his son Wes just yet.
We lost the flint scraper.
I do believe it is him.
Stop putting
stuff in the sand!
It was you who put it.
It's my turn to shine.
- What about my turn? He passed?
- Your turn is up.
- He passed?
- It's up to me.
- Your turn.
- The social aspect, the physical aspect,
- the mental aspect, I have everything.
- You have the mind of this rock!
This will be the ultimate test
for their relationship.
18 Americans
forced to cooperate while battling
the elements and each other.
They must learn to adapt
or they will be eliminated.
In the end, only one will win
the million dollars.
39 days,
18 people,
1 Survivor!
It's nice!
Let's talk about last night.
You all received flint.
Who managed to make the fire?
A lot of you!
You, at the end, did you make a fire?
- Yeah.
- What is your name?
Were you surprised
to achieve that, did...?
- Not surprised at all?
- Nope.
In general, people come here
without having ever tried to make a fire.
Jeff, if we want to do Survivor,
- you have to know how to make a fire.
- Exact.
You, in military uniform.
What is your name?
- Wes.
- Keith. Father and son.
- You didn't make a fire?
- Nope.
I had a problem.
We lost our scraper.
We lost it.
- We looked for him for an hour.
- It got off to a bad start.
But we used a rock,
and it started to work.
Until
the flint broke in two.
- So...
- It went downhill.
I happened to use flint.
It's pretty hard to break.
We did it!
Girls, what's your name?
- Natalie et Nadiya.
Sisters, obviously.
- Binoculars.
- Yeah.
Looking around you,
which, in your opinion,
could already be off to a bad start?
In The Amazing Race, we learned
not to trust appearances.
It depends on the tests.
There are so many factors.
This game is so social
everyone has their chance.
Because it's Blood vs. Water,
you will play against your relatives.
It's time to form the tribes.
I felt my stomach knot.
What to say to Natalie
just before she leaves?
Above all, not knowing how her tribe
would treat her was heartbreaking.
Let's discover our tribes.
Open, and see your colors.
If you have orange,
your name is Coyopa.
If you have blue,
your name is Hunahpu.
Say goodbye.
The game is started.
- Me too.
- Tear it all up!
Here we are.
I will play against my daughter.
It was quite moving,
it brings us back home.
That's the whole idea of ​​Blood vs. Water.
From the start,
Reed, a minute ago
you were with your loved one.
Now he is your opponent.
- Let him come! Let's go!
- Lord!
John, how's that for you?
A man wants to protect his wife,
that's what he's supposed to do, right?
On paper, yes.
It's a form of civil war,
brother against brother.
I watch a lot of sports
I'm pretty sure it's
John Rocker, the Braves pitcher.
And he was a jerk back then.
It might still be the case.
Jeremy, isn't that particularly hard
because you can no
longer do anything for your wife?
It's the only thing that's hard.
I want to help him.
- I want... She's my wife.
- I don't need his help.
- But she's strong.
- I'm going...
- She'll say that, but I'm still her husband.
- I'm solid, I can handle it.
And I don't need his help.
Looks like she doesn't
need your protection.
She says that all the time, but...
But what? I do not need it!
- It's over!
- When the game will start.
- I can handle myself.
Well, the game starts now.
Ready for your first
reward event?
Yeah!
This is how it will go.
One member from each tribe
will unravel a rope
in a wooden cube.
Attached to the rope, two rings.
With the first ring
you will catch a platform
and bring her back.
You will return to the cube,
untangle the rest of the rope,
and with the second ring,
bring back a second platform.
The first person to
take both platforms across the line
wins a reward for his tribe.
We will do paper-rock-scissors
to see who chooses first.
Let one member of each tribe
sit in the middle!
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
One two three!
The stone breaks the scissors.
Well, Hunahpu, who do you line up?
I can do it.
You're sure? Me too.
I should.
He looks confident. Go ahead!
- Will it be Jeremy?
- So be it.
Jeremy, come close to me.
Come on Jeremy!
Jeremy!
A perfect opportunity, from the outset,
to be a hero for your tribe,
to win a nice reward.
Want to know your opponent?
I do not care!
Yeah!
This is the first surprise of the game.
You confront your wife.
- Good!
- Let's go!
This way!
The couple who
verbally clashed the most
will fight the first battle.
There is more interesting.
Want to know what's at stake?
- Yes.
- Sure.
Fire, in the form of flint.
As well as a bag of beans.
Fire and food,
two essential elements here.
You will bring them back to your camp
from day one.
The loser of the event
will be sent to Exile Island.
Oh my God!
You will live there without shelter
and with very little to eat.
Alas, you will be absent from the camp
in the 1st moments, when
the crucial alliances
that can carry you in this game.
Nevertheless, you will return in time
for the immunity test.
You are not eliminated.
It's a real test of Blood vs. Water.
The only way to prove
your worth to your tribe
is to defeat your loved one
and send him into exile.
How do you feel now?
I am here to play.
Like all of us, right?
It's like that.
You will have it!
We install your belts
and we start. Let's go!
Good. The winner wins
the reward for his tribe.
The loser goes to Exile Island.
Jeremy versus Val.
- Husband versus wife.
- Go Val!
Come on Jeremy!
Survivors, ready?
- Come on Jeremy!
- Follow the rope wherever it goes!
Go Val! Go Val!
Val go for it!
Jeremy fonce!
Lots of adrenaline!
- They stand!
- Yeah, over!
Husband and wife face off!
- Keep the rope tight!
- Go around!
Jeremy has a bit of a lead,
Val has to get over it.
- You're doing very well!
- Above!
- Hook your leg!
- Jeremy has his first ring.
- Give slack!
- Above!
Val struggles to untangle this rope.
Jeremy is already throwing.
But grabbing this platform
is not that easy!
- Val struggles to climb.
- Come on, there you are!
Exile Island for the loser,
not a good start in the game!
That's how we do it
in Survivor!
Val again in the game!
She has her first ring.
There is a game!
Jeremy almost snagged his.
Will it work?
Nope! Very close!
- Yeah!
- Take it easy now.
Val hung up hers.
- She's making progress.
- Shoot it!
He unhooks.
Here, here!
Jeremy hung up his.
- He's starting to move.
- You're there!
Jeremy is doing a great job.
Jeremy has his first platform.
Hang up and get back to it!
Val, still after
her first platform.
You need enough rope
to do this.
- Jeremy extends his lead.
- Come on!
Val, still stuck
with too little rope.
- Jeremy has his second ring.
- Yeah!
Val throws her rope like a lasso,
like in a western!
Jeremy is now
on his 2nd and final platform.
Val hung up hers.
Jeremy hung up his.
Val is in front, Jeremy behind.
Jeremy unhooks.
Val stays in the game.
Well done, Val, get back to it!
Val needs to speed up.
Jeremy is about
to send his wife into exile.
Jeremy snagged
his second platform.
Can he bring her back?
That works.
Val tries to reach for
her second ring.
Perhaps in vain.
This may be the end.
Jeremy wins
the award for his tribe!
And sends his wife to the island of Exile!
Jeremy, come here!
From the outset, a big effort.
You have proven
what you bring to this tribe.
But in doing so, you send
your wife to Exile Island.
What do you feel?
I can not say anything.
On your side, Val, how does it
feel to see your husband like this?
I sympathize, but...
I'll be back. I am a fighter.
Jeremy, you win
fire for your tribe, in the form of flint.
Take it, it's well deserved.
- Cheer!
- And a bag of beans.
Now let's see who will be
with your wife on Exile Island.
You will choose
a person in your tribe
to accompany him.
Shit.
A crucial decision,
at the very beginning of the game...
I already know.
Who will go with her?
- Me?
- Yes.
And why?
'Cause I know
he knows how to light a fire,
that he is used to the great outdoors,
and that he can take care of her.
He's the guy who lost the scraper
and broke the flint!
It was his son's fault,
not his!
Bullshit!
- Keith, what do you think?
- No problem.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You seem moved.
It's true. I am for them.
I see what they are going through.
And I think all of us,
probably...
That before the end, each of us...
I don't know, I don't want to leave,
no more than him or her,
but we'll deal with it.
Switch places.
You go up, you go down.
Good. Your card to exile.
Thank you sir.
You will join your tribes in time
for the immunity test.
Val, Keith, on their way to exile!
Hunahpu, the map
to find your camp. Go for it!
I knew it
was Blood vs. Water,
but doing this to my wife
was my worst nightmare.
And now she's gone.
And it's my fault!
- With us!
- Yeah!
We are at home!
We walked
on this beautiful beach.
An epic "Survivor moment".
I have goose bumps.
It's really crazy, because all of a sudden...
"Oh, and now
we just have to get on with it!"
That's it, you have to go!
I'm happy, we have nails.
We have official "Survivor" bags!
Rusty things
to catch tetanus!
It's Christmas!
- Good start! Cheer!
- Yeah!
Yes, and thank you!
We will all find ourselves
in this situation at some point.
- I say.
- Each of us.
- I mean...
- You really rocked.
I have the greatest respect
for what you have done.
- I say.
- No one saw this coming.
- No, huh?
- Nobody.
Everyone congratulated me,
told me it was hard for me,
to confront my wife, and all that.
But everyone is happy that
I won the flint and the beans.
- Come!
- Let's go!
But in
testing against my wife,
I thought...
I was like,
"I'm not going to cry", you know?
And then, from day 1...
They are going to kill me, at home!
That we confront each other
like this hurts me.
But to see her go?
Oh-oh, man... Yeah!
She's my wife, I have to protect her.
And I didn't.
In Blood vs. Water,
you have to think of your loved ones.
For Val and me, in this game,
the important thing is our couple.
But it does
n't look good for her.
What are you thinking about?
I have a good contact with women,
I get on well with them.
So it's time
to go all out, time to play.
You look like a good guy,
I smell you good.
We have to stay united.
- I say.
- I mean...
We can be a strong pair,
a solid duo, hopefully.
OK fine!
That's what I think.
I was talking with Kelley.
Since there are nine of us,
we need five people.
What do you think of her?
- I like it.
- You like him? OK.
I appreciate Jeremy. The way
he fought today,
his emotion when he had to
send his wife into exile,
it shows that he has a good heart.
So if I have to choose
a twin, it's Jeremy.
Everyone loves firefighters.
What do you think?
And you?
You seem super honest,
so I'd like your sentiment.
- We need strength.
- I say.
- But also smart people.
When we were married and divorced
as much as I was,
you learn to trust your instincts.
And my gut tells me
to go to Jeremy.
This game is so moving.
The beginning of the game
immediately destabilized me,
but I feel
good now.
Everybody's with me,
I'm the popular type,
everyone wants
to date the prom king.
So it's perfect,
it will work.
Are we building a rear or...?
It's not a priority.
- The roof has priority.
- Oh, clearly.
We're in Survivor!
I have a machete!
And you open a coconut!
First day,
we take care of the essentials.
Trying to make a fire,
to have something in your belly,
and build a shelter.
- You are a student?
- Yes.
How old are you? I am 28 years old.
It's a young group,
with Wes, Baylor, Alec,
this is the young group.
Then there's me
Josh and Jaclyn,
more or less in the middle,
and then the other guy,
who's 40,
and dad is, like, 55, seriously!
- 32 years old is not old.
- Older than me!
It's true!
- As long as it's more than me...
- Yeah, exactly!
From the outset, it is clearly:
"OK, I'm 25 years older
than almost everyone here."
- How old are the others?
- You're not the oldest.
I'm an independent farmer,
I've been doing this all my life.
We don't get many visitors.
- What's the old man's name?
- Dale.
- I'll call him daddy.
- Too bright.
My biggest challenge in Survivor
is that I'm not used
to being in a group of strangers.
It's hard.
But you always have to
look for the positives.
On my first trip to the well,
I put the cover back in place,
and there is a small emblem.
It's not an idol
but it could be useful one day.
Why not?
I have to find another way
to fit into this tribe, fast.
The other way worked better.
I'm trying to make a fire
so we can boil some water.
It's smoking, but it's too wet
to create an ember.
That's why Bic
earns a billion a year!
I was getting more and more
pissed off at myself.
I'm supposed to be able to start
a fire, I've done that before.
Kid, I've done it
plenty of times with a magnifying glass.
Next!
We need fire
then we have two groups
with two different methods.
Dale uses
his glasses and the sun.
Which I've never seen work.
Frustrating bastard!
- And the second group,...
- There you are, Wes!
You and it is, you and it is!
...it's two of us
rubbing and rubbing
and try
to get something.
How are you, Dale?
Bon sang!
- I broke them.
- Oh, you did it on purpose?
Double power!
There's... Oh damn it!
You're right!
I broke my glasses in half,
and doubled the lenses
to double the magnification.
I sacrifice my ability to see
later in the game
to be able to light a fire.
- Let's go friends!
- Yeah! Yeah!
We have fire!
Dale, I love you!
To be frank, initially
we look at the old,
and we see an immediate target,
and then...
It was Dale who saved us all!
Day 1, when we
really needed it, it did.
Thanks, Dale, you're a badass!
I've said it at least ten times!
Dale the boss!
I don't have as much to worry
about socially anymore.
I'm the firemaker
now.
It takes me up
the food chain.
- Dale the chief!
- Dale the crack!
We literally owe you
our survival tonight.
Here we are.
Arriving on Exile Island
was a big shock.
The Coyopa tribe is
bonding.
If they have to eliminate someone,
I'll probably be the first.
And as a bonus, the island of Exile,
she fears a lot!
It's a lonely pile of rocks,
the ocean seems impractical,
you are really left with nothing.
Where do you want to start?
Yeah, let's see that.
I'm thinking of playing Survivor,
going all the way,
and boom! I'm on Exile Island!
I'm the first to squirt, with Val!
- Are we looking for shelter?
- Yeah.
It's not what I had expected.
I don't
even know my tribe yet.
I don't want to be here.
Is there something in this tree?
Maybe something to look into.
"Each must choose an urn."
You go-y!
I'll take this one.
He took his urn and I mine.
Everyone had a message
and started reading it.
Let's see.
I was so concerned
about my clue to an idol
that I didn't realize
his was blank.
What does it say?
Mine? It
's about something about the camp.
I think he was hoping
that I would say "Oh, read it!".
I wasn't going to do that.
There are other things.
Let's see.
Mine was blank.
I always have luck.
She beat around the bush.
It has to do with his tribe.
More power for her.
Me, I'm not going back to
his tribe, but to mine.
Are you from Louisiana?
I never made it past
northern Arkansas.
Really?
I would be completely out of place
in Massachusetts.
. I saw this Boston t-shirt.
- Yeah.
And I saw his Cambridge t-shirt.
Yes, he is a firefighter in Cambridge.
No kidding!
Say, we have something in common.
- Are you a firefighter?
- And Wes too.
It's not true!
It is very true!
I found
out her husband is a firefighter.
It will create a link.
It will surely be a big plus.
Back at camp,
I'll go see Jeremy.
See where it fits.
But who knows?
I don't know what
I'll be stepping into there.
All eight hate me.
And that's the end
of my career in Survivor.
Where has everyone gone?
- Jeremy and...
- I don't know.
I didn't want to, but it took
that I take over
the construction of the shelter.
I'm glad
everyone helps me.
- They had better bring back lots of coconuts.
- Yeah.
There was a lot of work,
I laid the foundations of the structure.
It was important to be above
the ground, to have fresh ocean air.
It will support people, is it strong?
- That's the plan.
- OK.
- You know what I mean?
- No, I like it.
I almost passed out while
building it, hope it holds up.
I hope the tribe appreciates
my efforts on the shelter.
- Look at this!
- I'm proud of you.
I've been a successful model
for a few years.
I don't hit in Europe,
but my face is known
in quite a few places.
But I'm not here to
be a model, but a Survivor.
I took the shelter in hand.
- I had never built one, but...
- You rock!
Lord!
I'm not sure why
Drew thinks he's in charge.
He's a little too arrogant.
The brave boy.
Great!
Being the woman that I am...
I'm dating John Rocker,
and he was playing at the top level.
He's an alpha male
with a capital "a".
So I understand
the mentality of guys.
And Drew... He's a young jerk.
Badabing, badaboum!
Do you know John's last name?
- Nope. And you?
- I think it is...
- I think I saw him...
- You think he's famous?
Yeah, I think he's a sportsman,
but I'm not sure.
I had my doubts about John
from the start.
I thought to myself that
I had already seen it somewhere.
I realized he had played
baseball with the Atlanta Braves.
My favorite team!
And that was when they were on top!
What's your last name, John?
- Wetlands?
- Yeah.
- You're sure?
100%?
I was hoping to remain anonymous
in this game, to go unnoticed.
If I was recognized,
I wanted to lie,
because I have rather lacked anonymity for
the past 18 years.
What are you thinking about?
I think it starts with "R".
Wes pinched me.
It didn't take long.
After two or three hours,
"Your name is John, huh?".
"And your last name?"
Are there five letters?
- There are seven.
- No, six!
Y'en to Sept.
OK. You look like someone who...
...was in your school?
- No, that I saw on TV.
- Oh.
He was a boss.
Back then.
- When the Braves were good.
- When they were awesome.
OK, you got me.
It seemed to me.
I didn't know if you were going...
...to pretend.
- Keep that for you.
- Yeah.
"I'm trying to lay low.".
I am happy.
He's from Georgia, me from Louisiana,
I knew who he was...
There is a kind of connection.
I play baseball...
I couldn't fool
everyone. I will have tried.
Wes knowing my secret
isn't necessarily a good thing.
At the first tip,
I'll be a little nervous.
I might as well try to eliminate Wes.
Is it better if you close your eyes?
No. It's a burning sensation.
It started suddenly,
just lying here...
All of a sudden,
my eyes ignite.
And now it's burning.
And I cry constantly.
Survivor
always has a dirty trick in store for you.
"Ah, here you are in the middle
of nowhere, you're not used to it!"
"And you have this!"
We are here,
we must take it and survive.
I'm in Survivor,
that's what I'll do.
Josh has such red eyes!
I hope I don't catch what he has.
It looks horribly painful.
He can't even
really open them anymore.
Not a good sign, after three days.
There is a plant here
who, in case of contact,
makes it itchy or something?
My only idea is those leaves
we touched.
Oh, the sap!
It is this plant, the sap!
We pulled them out
instead of cutting them.
Do you think that's it?
I'm telling you.
It is realized that the sheets
used for the roof
have a poisonous sap,
or something like that.
So let's take them off.
We are therefore busy removing
them and moving them away from the camp.
My eyes are telling you
to keep this as far away as possible.
We got poisonous sap,
scorpions...
There could well be a cougar
in the corner without our knowing it.
There is danger, far from
what I know and had imagined.
Come on, thank you...
"Are you a female? Let's go!".
I wish I had a tail.
I've always done the andouille.
But I'm deeper
than I look.
Nobody knows
what's going on with me.
In February, my father learned
that he had a brain tumor.
Just there.
It is incurable.
I thought about it a lot, of course.
I think I have no more tears.
Knowing that we don't have
much time left to spend together,
deciding to come to Survivor
was very difficult.
But my dad
is a big fan of Survivor,
and I would not have come
without his blessing.
I just hope I can
watch it with him.
And that he will be proud of me.
Over here everyone!
Now here are Val and Keith,
back from Exile Island.
- This way!
- Yeah, Keith!
- I told you you'd hold on.
- Thanks.
Val, two days in exile.
How was it?
It's a desolate place,
with little foliage.
But this girl from the north and
this guy from the south hit it off.
It went well.
We can imagine that
many relationships have been created
during your two days of absence.
Hope you find
your place in your tribes.
Ready for your first
immunity test?
Yeah!
Today
you will climb a giant tower.
At my top, both tribes
will crawl under an obstacle.
Then you will work together
to collect three bags.
They contain coins
needed to reach the top.
For the first wall,
you will use a rope.
For the second wall,
you will use pegs.
For the third,
there will only be mutual aid.
Once at the top,
four members of each tribe
will solve a puzzle.
The tribe that finishes
first wins immunity.
This is what you covet
in this game.
With immunity, you are protected.
Without, you are in danger.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be the 1st eliminated
from Blood vs. Water.
Coyopa, you also still play
for fire, in the form of flint.
One minute to organize yourself,
and we'll begin.
Let's go! For immunity!
Survivors, ready?
People mix
under there, I like!
This is your first opportunity
to introduce yourself to the other tribe.
Alec has already hurt himself.
Come on!
People cut themselves.
This land is unfriendly.
One bag at a time, collaborating.
Baylor takes care of it for Coyopa.
Natalie takes care of it for Hunahpu.
Julie's turn to come up.
Baylor takes care of the second bag.
Baylor is now handling
the third sack for Coyopa.
Go girl, go!
- Go Julie!
- Julie has her second bag.
Kelley's turn.
Baylor has all three, go for it!
Let a person
start to open first!
John takes the rope for Coyopa
and goes to try to hang it.
Kelley has the third sack
for Hunahpu.
There is a learning phase.
You have to throw.
John tries a new approach.
It's way harder than it looks.
This rope is very heavy.
The hanging window
is very narrow.
John hooks it up for Coyopa!
He climbs first.
Use rope tension!
- John came up.
- Come on Wes!
Wes climbs in turn.
Drew takes over for Hunahpu.
Keith was unsuccessful.
Wes came up.
Coyopa took the lead.
More slack.
Come on, we'll get there!
Nadiya came up.
And this is Val.
Drew narrowly misses for Hunahpu.
And this is Jaclyn.
She is hesitant.
We cannot hesitate.
Drew made it for Hunahpu!
Climb that wall!
Drew flies over this wall.
- This is Jon.
- Come on boy!
Come on, Josh, go!
On and goes, on and goes!
And here is Josh.
Go to the next wall!
Pitons now.
First peak!
Hunahpu tries to come back up.
Josh climbs first
with the pitons, no problem.
- Come on!
- Its good!
Very good collaboration at Coyopa.
Keith rode for Hunahpu.
Jeremy, the last to ride
for Hunahpu.
Take out the pegs!
- Come on!
- There you are, there you are!
Come on!
Wes, the last up for Coyopa.
Now we gotta
climb that third wall
as you can!
Hunahpu is still
on the second wall.
Nice collaboration at Coyopa.
John is a human pyramid,
letting people climb on him
to reach the top.
Hunahpu is still at the pitons.
Here is Drew. All of a sudden,
the test tightens.
- You go-y, you go-y!
- OKAY.
And here is John.
Wow, that's a lot of weight!
Women shoot John!
Superb collective effort by Coyopa!
Come on!
Julie rode for Hunahpu.
Let's go, Alex goes there running.
Josh grabbed it.
Coyopa is upstairs.
Attack the puzzle!
Four people!
Hunahpu always strives
to climb this wall. More than two.
Jon, helped by Drew,
there he is upstairs.
More than Drew now,
he has to climb this wall.
And he does!
Go on!
The two tribes are tackling
a very big puzzle.
It is very complicated.
It is a symmetrical puzzle.
These coins will go
in a lot of different places.
Are they in the right place?
You won't know until the end.
Coyopa is making a lot of progress,
provided you are right.
It's here! It's here!
It does not fit!
Coyopa thought he was at the end,
but it doesn't fit!
There is a mistake!
- Flip it!
- Yes! Yes!
Hunahpu believes to have found!
Nope! So close,
and yet not!
Try something else!
What is frustrating,
it's that we believe we are progressing,
and we realize... that we are not.
Go! Go! Go!
The Hunahpu are very excited
about their progress!
They are getting closer.
Are they right this time?
It seems like!
Yes! Hunahpu wins immunity!
Well done Julia!
Hunahpu, congratulations!
Missy, it must be hard to be protected
when your daughter isn't.
Sure, it's hard, Jeff.
It's my little daughter.
But she's super-super strong,
and I know that no matter what,
she will be fine.
Natalie. In general, you are
with your sister all the time.
Tonight she is in danger.
I say. All day,
I thought a lot about Nadiya.
It's like half
my heart is there.
It's really very hard.
Advice tonight.
Someone will be the first eliminated.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
It could well be me tonight.
I would be very surprised.
I alone made the fire.
But I'm the oldest of the bunch.
You never know what will happen.
Well done everyone!
Does it look like the Taj Mahal?
Hey, you sure did!
I just joined
my original tribe,
and we started with a test.
Boom, that's done!
Then we get here,
I see what they've done,
and it looks like
they worked well together.
I need to know
a few names.
- I'm Reed.
- Reed.
- Julie.
I didn't know what to expect.
To make my place
in this tribe, having been absent,
I will try
to sneak in, to adapt.
For now,
just remember their names!
I know Jeremy,
and that's about it.
I wanted to talk to you,
because I owe you a debt.
- I wouldn't say that.
- But if.
I owe you one.
- It wasn't a chore.
- But I owe you one.
Just before the test,
Val and I looked at each other.
She gave me a sign
that she was fine.
I knew then that
Keith had taken care of her.
I don't know
how far this will take her,
but I feel indebted to him.
- I pulled you out of line...
- Yeah.
- ...and I'll put you back in.
- OK.
- You're one of us!
- Jeremy is half on my side.
He's a firefighter, so am I.
Firefighters are a brotherhood.
But the other seven? No idea.
In a day or two, we'll know.
We'll see what happens.
We often swim in the sea,
then we go there, there is a kind of lake,
it's soft water, it cleans.
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
Welcome Val!
Glad you're here!
- Thanks!
- You're welcome!
After losing,
I immediately thought...
I haven't been able to play yet,
and it may be over already.
So as soon as I found out
where the well was,
my clue was talking about,
I went there.
I have to find this idol.
So, Natalie, how is it
compared to The Amazing Race?
- Nadiya.
- Nadiya, pardon!
Go on!
It's completely different.
In The Amazing Race,
you are given everything you need,
and basically it's up to you
to figure out what to do.
Nadiya is a known element.
She was in The Amazing Race.
She showed
that she can betray someone.
For the others, I do not know.
Nadiya proved it. We have seen it.
- Val is the easiest vote.
- Yeah.
She's only
been here a few hours.
But I
would like to give him a chance.
- I would say Nadiya.
- No problem.
Because I know his strategy
in The Amazing Race.
I don't know The Amazing Race.
In The Amazing Race,
there is the U-turn, one can betray.
I saw her do that,
I know a little about the game.
I respect the game, it's the rules.
But better to betray before being betrayed.
I agree.
Dale and the other guys think
Nadiya should leave,
because she was
in The Amazing Race.
And... Of course we say yes!
Then Nadiya approached me,
a few minutes later.
- I am with you.
- I knew it.
And I know Natalie
is with your guy over there.
I am sure of it.
We think the same of you.
We are leaving.
We'll discuss that a bit later.
As soon as someone
approaches me, I say to myself:
"Thank you Lord! They are coming to me!".
And you know...
This is the position
I wanted to have.
I succeeded.
It was one of my goals
"I want to work with you.".
I counted you among the girls.
"I counted you among the girls.".
My friend will tell you:
this is one of the worst things
anyone can say to me.
But I don't blame him.
People
always put you in boxes.
I'll keep my options open,
I have quite a few possibilities.
I have my head on the block.
I wasn't there, I didn't have...
...no way to create links,
I understand that.
Now here's the thing.
Let's create a female alliance.
We can rally a guy.
Don't want to write history?
It's about time...
- ...girls show...
- Damn, yeah!
I like it!
Seriously!
And so, the girls get together.
It was an opportunity to realize
that we have to be welded,
and that if not,
our options are limited.
Which guy will join us?
We need the majority.
I've already seen Josh, that's enough.
- It's...
- Oh yes, of course!
He is with us, believe me.
I definitely wanted to
work with Josh, the gay guy.
We already count him as a girl.
Let's think...
...to guys we don't need.
We can win events without him.
- He lit the fire!
- So what?
We'll have flint tonight.
Yeah, let's do it!
The plan is to eliminate Dale,
because it is thought to be useless
in trials.
One two three...
If I'm not the girls,
I'll do what Josh does.
I haven't been able to
chat with him yet.
of what his plans are.
But I want to hear it first.
Alright, so what's going on?
Lord, many things!
- The girls took me to the well.
- OK.
They want to vote Dale.
- And what do you want to do?
- Vote with you.
- OK.
- At this point, what do you think?
- Did you talk to the boys?
- They're talking about Nadiya.
But we have to see this.
There are many things in the air.
And I feel
like that relies a lot on me.
I feel right in
between the alliance of guys
and that of the girls.
That's the first damn tip, and...
I feel...
As a fan of the show,
this is an important moment.
But what matters is knowing
who will take me the furthest.
At this point, I don't know.
Sometimes those with the deciding vote
end up in the worst position.
I don't even know
if I'm going to decide
before the board
I'm going to vote for.
Behind you, torches.
Grab one
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If your fire goes away, so do you.
John, are you surprised?
It's so hard to come here,
three days can
seem like an eternity,
and before you even realize it,
you eliminate someone.
It seems very fast,
but that's the game.
It is the rule.
Unfortunately, here we are,
while the Blues are
probably partying on the beach.
It's hard.
There is no obvious choice
an insufferable lazy
or a real jerk.
Nadiya, tell me
about the spirit of the tribe.
It seems to me that we got along well
from the start.
And suddenly we have
this huge decision to make
that none of us are ready
to take so quickly.
But you have to look at the attitude
of people, their physical skills.
I learned to always persevere.
Never give up. Life is hard.
Will you be sad,
or smile,
make the best
of the situation and move on?
If they give you lemons,
make lemonade, right?
Make margaritas out
of it, preferably.
It can enable a tribe
to overcome adversity.
Josh, are you okay?
It's a very positive
and upbeat way to play Survivor.
Yes. We must keep this optimism
and this motivation permanently.
It is essential in survival.
Because if you stop being positive,
you are dead.
Nadiya, I have to ask you.
What is the difference between 3 Days
of Survivor and The Amazing Race?
Oh, Jeff, that's so different!
In The Amazing Race,
you are told exactly what to do.
"This is your island,
do what you want with it!"
You know!
Survivor took all the essentials away from me.
Water, shelter, food...
And also, and not
least, my twin sister.
She is my only family in America.
We only have us.
But for the next X days,
here is my family.
And I'm surprised,
we're doing well.
I am proud of our tribe.
Val, how was it for you?
You spent most
of those three days in exile.
It's stressful, because I do
n't really know these people.
I haven't really
had time to bond.
But exile also has its advantages.
Time to explore,
find things,
hopefully that puts my
mind at ease, regardless of the outcome.
Jaclyn, who quickly bonded?
Who did you see get along real quick?
The boys, especially.
bonded immediately.
So, Dale,
how was it for you?
Because typically, the elders
are often easy targets.
Yes, I'm 20 years older
than most of them.
We have different interests.
It's hard to find
topics of conversation.
So what do you do,
knowing your age
can be enough to get you eliminated?
First, I prove my worth to the tribe.
That's why I took
my reading glasses, and...
This is Jeff's rule:
fire is life.
I tried to light a fire,
and after 90 minutes
it didn't work,
so I broke them
to double the lentils.
And it still took 1h15
sun to light a fire.
What is the feeling when finally,
you see flames?
An immense relief,
because it is the first need.
Without fire, you cannot boil
water or cook food.
We would have really suffered.
Wes, are there one or two people
who are more attractive to others,
whose opinion
and conversation are sought?
Yes, I think Josh
is the most popular.
Everyone talks to him, asks him
what's going on or if there are any problems.
We speak to him and he tells you that
he understands,
May he support and sympathize with you.
He is empathetic.
Jeff, I agree.
It has the advantage of being
between the girls and the boys.
For me, he is one of the girls.
Because he's gay?
- Or because...
- I think the fact that he's gay,
it helps. Clearly, I will
never see a straight person as "a girlfriend".
Josh, that's an interesting position.
Women like you,
men like you.
Do you feel pressure?
If the four girls are together,
the other four guys too,
and me stuck in the middle,
so my decision is crucial.
But that is surely not
what is happening.
But it could.
- That's always the big question.
- Yes always.
Well, it's time to vote.
Wes, over to you.
We all love you, darling.
You have a great personality.
But you have way too much
The Amazing Race experience.
Because you are isolated.
I will count the votes.
Oh my God!
It's too intense!
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Nadiya.
One Dale vote, one Nadiya vote,
one Baylor vote.
Dale.
Nadiya.
Two Nadiya votes,
two Dale votes, one Baylor vote.
Dale. Three votes for Dale.
Nadiya. New equality.
Three Nadiya votes,
three Dale votes, one Baylor vote.
Nadiya.
Four Nadiya votes,
three Dale votes, one Baylor vote.
First Person Eliminated
- San Juan del Sur...
Nadia. Bring me your torch.
Nadiya, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
I think the message is clear.
You lost both events,
a third of the tribe received votes,
this tribe is still looking for itself.
I'm after him now.
Period.
I feel cheated by John.
Officially, you give up.
I'm glad he's gone.
You just lost a limb.
It's the war.
We will fight until the end.
Count on it!
If you're a man,
I'll knock your teeth out.
This is my 2nd time going out
first, it sucks!
Everything is possible.
We can have regrets,
but it's like that.
I'm not surprised,
but I'm clearly disappointed.
I hope Natalie will win.
It will be hard,
without someone to support him.
But I will support her until the end.