english from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Welcome to
- Blood vs. Water.
Nine pairs of relatives
were forced to face each other,
and the Isle of Exile
was back.
During the last
reward event...
And There you go!
...Julie beat
her boyfriend, John Rocker,
and chooses Jeremy, Val's husband,
to accompany her into exile.
In exile, John promised Jeremy
to watch over his wife.
You protect Val,
and I will protect Julie.
Bargain.
During the immunity test...
- Go Val!
- Smother her!
...Coyopa continued to lose.
Val falls!
Hunahpu wins immunity
and remain undefeated!
On the camp, John
found the idol of immunity...
Bingo, guys!
...and kept his promise
to Jeremy to protect Val.
If I want to protect Julie,
I have to protect Val.
Play this idol and everything will be fine.
But Val was lying to John.
She had no idol.
And Josh was suspicious.
John and Val isolated themselves.
They had never done that.
On council, he changed
his vote from Baylor to Val.
Sorry.
Val. Bring me your torch.
Val, the tribe has spoken.
Sixteen remain.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
I am definitely vaccinated
with the idea that I risk nothing.
Now it's
"Baylor fights alone",
and not "Baylor relies on Josh
to talk to others".
I came very close
to surprise elimination tonight.
- Is there any water left?
- Nope.
We should never run out of water.
At this point, I don't
trust anyone,
but I'm always open
to play with someone.
- I knew she didn't have an idol.
- Yeah.
She had to do something swollen,
and the best way to do it,
- was to pretend to have an idol.
- Yeah.
When Jeremy sees that his wife
is gone, he will be pissed.
But I told her to play
her idol, that she was targeted.
She did not do it.
What else could I do?
I leaked information.
If my five allies knew that,
they wouldn't be happy.
I wonder who changed his vote.
It was me.
Sorry, I didn't have
time to tell you.
I was... I redid the accounts,
I said to myself, no!
- I had to do it.
- That was smart.
I had to vote for Val.
Just before the board, I realized
that Jaclyn and Val would be voting Baylor.
And that wasn't the plan.
I think
John was no stranger to it.
He walked
with Val before the council.
And he had never
spent time with her.
I like the alliance of the five guys.
- I think it's solid.
- Oh yeah!
John's credibility
plummeted in my eyes,
the last 24 hours.
But we'll probably keep
playing dude alliance,
and unless something really crazy,
Jaclyn and Baylor are probably
next to jump.
The monsoon is coming. Maybe
not today, but it's coming.
- We need to reinforce the shelter.
- Yeah.
- We need a collective effort.
I try to warn my tribe
that we need to
cover the roof of the shelter.
Looks like gruyere.
It won't be fun when
the tropical storms arrive.
- Natalie, do we need a way?
- Yes.
We redesigned the roof
and started weaving
palm leaves.
We gave lessons and put everyone
to work, even the boys.
So. Shoot well. You're there.
It's tedious.
Except Drew. After a minute,
he was fed up.
He must have taken a nap.
Weaving is not for me.
I have other strengths, but...
Weaving is not one of them.
Drew sleeps a lot.
If my son acted like that...
Better keep quiet.
I sure can't
say that on camera.
I would give her a little...
You know.
We always practice spanking,
us in the South.
Serious? You just tickle me
when I fall asleep?
Everyone works, so...
Sorry to work where you sleep.
What did you do today, Drew?
Tell me something you did.
You spent the day
watching us weave.
Everyone else worked.
Okay, Natalie, I get it.
How can we come here
with complete strangers,
without feeling the need
to do their part?
Drew is dead weight.
I'm not used
to such egomaniacs,
so unconcerned about
what's going on.
So my tolerance is very limited.
But it's good for the game.
He won't win the million.
Drew does anything.
I was planning to take him further,
because he's a moron.
But I won't be able to.
If he is already physically collapsing,
on the 20th day, he will tell me:
"Listen, I want to go home,
I can't take it anymore, Jeremy."
"Take my million,
I'll give it to you!"
Over here everyone!
Hunahpu, discover
the new Coyopa tribe.
Val was eliminated at the last council.
No matter.
Many reactions
among the Hunahpu.
Especially from you, Jeremy,
finding out about your wife's departure.
What happens is that
men take control.
They will try to eliminate all
the strong women who threaten them.
You must turn against them.
This is what you must do.
Because you are next.
John, this is one of the levels of this game,
when it comes to loved ones.
She's your wife,
your brother, your sister.
I feel bad
and I apologize to Jeremy.
I gave him my man word
that I would protect his wife.
I argued as much as I could,
but I couldn't
convince my allies,
and I finally had to follow them.
All the guys, we went, "What?"
I had suspected him
of working with Val,
but he just admitted it,
right in the middle of the arena!
Ready for
today's reward event?
This is how it will go.
One member of each team
will ride on an unstable track.
Using an oar,
he will transfer squares of wood
side to side.
If you drop a piece,
you will have to go back to the start,
and take another from the heap.
The first to transfer
six pieces from one end to the other
earns the reward for his tribe.
- Want to know what's at stake?
- Yeah.
Comfort. A tarp,
a hammock, mattresses,
pillows, blankets.
Or you can trade that
for what Hunahpu
traded for flint
last time.
A very nice fishing kit.
Two huge rewards,
and the choice is yours.
Let's do paper-rock-scissors
to see who will have the advantage
to choose first.
It is Coyopa who will choose.
I think my dad
would be bad at that.
Let's choose Wes.
Wes is going to face his father Keith.
You will succeed, Wes!
You go-y Keith!
Take a seat, let's get started.
Well, on and go.
Huge in-game reward.
Father against son.
Reward for the winner,
Exile Island for the loser.
Survivors, ready?
You go-y, Wes, you go-y!
You have to find the balance
between speed and precision.
Bravo, Keith.
Calm. Its good.
Wes has the premiere.
A nice big pancake, Wes!
Keith approaches his first.
The son would like to beat the father,
and dad would like to remind his son
that age brings experience and wisdom.
Take your time, Keith!
- Keith is well reassembled.
- Well done, Keith!
Keith poses his first,
Wes poses his first.
- And There you go!
- Well done, Keith!
Yeah, well done!
Equality!
Huge in-game reward!
- Good, Wes.
- Keeps the oar stable.
Keith, very stable, puts his second...
- Great, Keith!
- ...piece of wood, go get the 3rd one!
Calm down, Keith, just like that!
Wes has his second, he's picking up the pace.
He starts to speed up a bit.
Keith, it's okay,
carry on quietly.
- Right, Wes.
- It's okay, Wes.
- Cheer!
- That's it, Wes!
Gently!
- Calm!
- Gently!
Keith places his third.
Well done, Keith!
Wes places his third.
Tie, 3-3!
We are halfway!
At some point,
Wes will have to act to get back up.
Or hope that his father makes
a mistake... And here he is acting!
Nice shot, Wes!
Well done, kid!
Keith moves the rail a lot,
but he does well.
- Not too fast, Keith.
- Slow down, slow down!
Very nice recovery from Keith!
Wes has his fourth, he's going back.
Keith has his fourth, he's going back.
Wes is now in the lead for Coyopa.
Keith has his fifth.
The wind picks up.
Gently.
Nice recovery from Wes!
Keith fails.
Keith has to go
get another one.
- Go on!
- Look at the kid!
A fifth for Wes.
Keep it up, Wes!
Coyopa has yet to win
an event all season.
Wes takes his sixth.
Go ahead my guy!
The Coyopa can smell
their first victory.
Keith has his fifth.
Go Keith!
- Here we are.
- Come on Wes!
He must go to the end
and stretch his pole.
He's going to let go, Keith, it's good!
Will the curse be lifted?
Wes wins the award for Coyopa!
Hit me five!
You too, Baylor!
It was tight. I'm happy.
I'm thirty years older than him, but...
I wasn't far.
You are moved again.
Well, I mean...
To see him progress, this young man...
- Are you proud of him?
- Oh yeah, and how!
You usually share
those kinds of emotions, Wes?
No way.
I don't see these feelings...
I mean...
I haven't seen it like this
than on the death of my great-grandfather,
his grandfather.
Everything is fine, everything is fine.
Good. Come over here, Wes.
You have two big decisions
to make. First of all,
you must decide who in your tribe
will accompany your father into exile.
Who will it be?
I think I'll take Josh.
Why Joe?
I think he'll be nice
to my dad.
I get on well with Josh, so...
Maybe my dad
will get along with him.
- Alright, switch places.
- OK.
Its good.
You couldn't have done better.
Josh, Keith, you're off
to Exile Island.
You'll be back in time
for the next immunity test.
Here is the map to find the island.
- See you later!
- See you soon!
Coyopa, another big decision.
What reward will you take?
The comfort or the fishing kit?
The fishing kit!
Come get your reward
and go!
Maybe the wheel has turned.
I did everything I could, brother.
I swear to you.
Hunahpu, I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
"I did everything I could."
My eye!
If you had,
she would still be here.
I'm after him now.
- Sorry, Jeremy.
- How are you.
It's not your fault.
Julie left alone.
But why is she crying?
This John is not his John.
- Nope.
- That's not her John.
- He plays his game.
- Yeah.
They have to start saying to each other
that they have to come after him.
- Because he's in control.
- This is what I...
I was pissed not to see Val.
For John Rocker had said
to me, shaking my hand,
that he would take care of her.
He turned his back on our deal.
So even
if he's not in my tribe,
I need him to go.
You don't know
who John Rocker is. Me, I know it.
You don't know.
Tell us!
It's a launcher.
He was pitching for the Atlanta Braves.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Let me tell you
exactly who this guy is.
He said
racist and gay stuff.
And he got in big trouble.
- He's intolerant, then.
- Yeah.
On the ground, he looked askance at people
, they spat on him.
- You remember it?
- Sure.
I was giving Julie
the benefit of the doubt.
At least his loved one is still there.
This is not the case for everyone.
We should be crying.
I have no sympathy for Julie.
She tries to cover him
and cover herself.
Knowing that John
made racist and homophobic remarks,
I want the other team
to have the balls to oppose him.
I bet he wouldn't mind
being eliminated.
- Yeah.
- I am sure.
I feel very alone after that.
If everyone believes Jeremy
when he says John is in control,
then John could become a target.
If they believe what he said,
so it doesn't matter what I do.
John...
...is my partner in this game and...
You have to play your own game.
You are here for that.
Yes, but with what happened,
no matter what I do.
Everything is distorted, it's a mess.
I never thought,
even in my wildest dreams,
that Blood vs. Water
would also be difficult.
I know it's a game
but knowing me
in this situation by his fault,
it's hard.
Alright, Josh, this is where we're going.
- Thank you for inviting me...
- Yeah.
...your house!
Exile Island
is full of rocks.
She's tough, and she sucks.
I'm probably going to sleep
on rocks tonight.
But at least we have a clue
to find the immunity idol.
Choose one, but...
Are we sharing information?
I didn't think, the first time,
when Val and I were here.
She got the clue,
and I got a blank piece of paper.
I tell myself that this time,
I will have something.
- I don't think I have anything.
- Yeah.
- Like me the other time.
- PQ, that's what I have!
Yeah!
Yeah, here it is.
"An idol is hidden on your camp."
- So John...
- John could have it.
- And Jeremy at my house.
- Yes.
Exactly.
Few people came here.
And only Jeremy,
besides me, on my team.
So I have to go back,
find the idol,
and only Jeremy stands in my way.
I'll tell you, we can go
get some snails.
Oh yeah!
We break them up and eat them.
Yeah, clear!
This is delicious. I like.
I don't want to stop anymore.
Neither do I.
People would be surprised
that we get along so well.
A hillbilly from Louisiana
and a homo from New York...
You don't expect them to
relax and have fun together.
I feel good here.
Eating snails,
passing the time, in great company.
Josh and I are night and day.
He looks like a good boy.
He's just not my good boy.
It's cool to be able to hang out
with people from other walks of life
that we would not otherwise encounter.
If not, how to change and evolve?
I'm going to go test my bed,
see if i can...
Improve it?
Josh is on one side of the fire
and I'm on the other.
We're not snuggling up to
each other tonight.
Zut!
I don't see many
Josh's in Louisiana!
And how about
from another catfish?
- Oh yeah!
- Let's eat them all!
We won!
We managed
to win today.
And we got the fishing kit.
- Great, John!
- Well done, man!
I try to feed the tribe.
I hope they like it,
maybe it will make me look good.
Maybe I'm starving
but it's delicious.
Yeah, this one is really good.
Hats off to John
for catching fish.
It was good to swallow some protein.
I feel that we are going to be a hit
at the next test.
It's a game, don't forget that.
I say.
I'm glad you got
along well with the other guys,
but you don't matter to them.
Think about it.
I know, I clearly think about it.
Jaclyn would easily join us.
So, the four of us.
For now the guys team up
to eject the girls,
so i thought
about what i could say
to push the younger guys
towards the idea of ​​eliminating John.
John is angry and negative and...
It's just negativity, to me.
He's pretty cool.
But some aspects
seem to be like a virus.
Yeah.
I think we could
eliminate John if we wanted to.
So do it!
Think headcount, okay?
So think about...
You act like
we don't think about it!
Sometimes I have doubts.
Baylor is the most misplaced,
and she knows it.
So she tries to get out
of it in every possible way.
But we have a solid group of guys,
and we always plan to
fire the girls one by one.
It sucks to have to lie to her,
- but it could still be useful.
- Yeah.
Let 's focus
on winning the race.
I agree, you have to.
Over here everyone!
Now let's welcome Josh and Keith back
after their night together in exile.
Ready for a new
immunity test?
Yeah!
First, I take back the idol.
Thank you, Natalie.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will be split
into pairs tied together.
On my signal, a duo from each tribe
dash under an
obstacle course to retrieve a ball.
You will then try
to throw it into a basket.
The first team to score
three points wins immunity,
is out of the vote.
The losers will go to the board
where a third person
will be eliminated from the game.
In each tribe,
one person will not participate,
to have an even number of players.
Who will it be?
Keith will not participate at Hunahpu.
Coyopa, who will not participate?
It will be Dale.
The two oldest.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, one minute
to get organized
and we'll start.
- Sorry, Dale.
- Its good.
Good. On and go.
Who goes there for Hunahpu?
Jon and Natalie,
against Josh and Baylor for Coyopa.
The first duo to put a basket
mark for his tribe.
We go to three points.
Let's go. Survivors, ready?
- Let's go!
- Go on!
Josh and Baylor go
straight to the ground.
Josh rushes, Baylor right behind him.
Get over him!
Its good.
Jon and Natalie go fast too.
Josh has the ball first.
Go Josh!
Jon has the ball for Hunahpu.
Now we have to come back.
The belt, the belt!
Jon will shoot for Hunahpu.
Go on!
Just missed.
Baylor shoots for Coyopa.
Far too short.
Need more height.
Jon found his ball for Hunahpu.
Josh and Baylor are looking for theirs.
- Aim!
- Jon will try again.
- He scores! Hunahpu leads 1-0.
- Cheer!
Good boy! Good boy!
Wes and Alec
against Missy and Julie.
Coyopa must equalize.
Survivors, ready? Go!
Wes and Alec are quickly
on their elbows and knees.
They are not afraid to get dirty.
- Alec rammed Julie.
- Go Julie!
- He hit a girl, John!
Catch them!
Missy and Julie arrive at their ball.
Wes and Alec already have theirs.
Coyopa brand! Tie, 1-1!
Well done, Wes!
Next duets!
Drew and Reed versus John and Jaclyn.
Survivors, ready? Go!
- From below!
- Come on Drew!
John and Jaclyn have long legs.
They just step over.
Go Reed!
John is looking for trouble!
- What fair play!
- He's a bad player.
You'll bruise back at camp,
but if you return with immunity,
you will not suffer from it!
Go John!
John will shoot for Coyopa,
he could give them the advantage.
And he does!
Coyopa leads 2-1.
Next duos, come closer!
Josh and Baylor come back,
against Jeremy and Kelley.
Coyopa leads 2-1.
We go to three points.
Coyopa could win now.
Go on!
Survivors, ready?
Stay close to him, Baylor!
He drags Baylor in this course.
Jeremy and Kelley
charge into this course.
Lots of effort
just to get to the ball.
Jeremy has the ball for Hunahpu.
We have to come back now.
Come on, Josh!
Baylor has it! You have to shoot!
She shoots!
Missed narrowly!
When you miss,
you have to get the ball back.
Jeremy shoots. Can it get there?
Jeremy shoots for Hunahpu and scores!
Tie, 2-2!
We go to three points.
Following duets.
- Do we do the same?
- Wes and Alec are coming back.
- Its good!
- Come on Jon! Go Nat!
Against Jon and Natalie for Hunahpu.
There is a tie, 2-2.
The next tribe that scores
gain immunity.
Talk, communicate!
Survivors, ready?
Coyopa must score now,
or it's over,
and this will be their third
consecutive board.
- Wes has a falling out with Natalie.
- Yes!
Coyopa still hasn't
won immunity.
They know they have to score.
They waste no time.
Jon comes back first,
he'll shoot for Hunahpu.
He misses.
Wes shoots and misses for Coyopa.
Huge challenge. Coyopa
does not want to return to the council.
Hunahpu never went there.
- They don't want to start tonight.
- Wes, push it!
It's getting confused down there!
Go on!
- Its good!
- Let's go!
- They're stuck.
- Its good!
Go Jon!
Jon has it for Hunahpu.
He can win right there.
And he does!
Hunahpu wins immunity
for the third time in a row!
Step up a gear!
You eliminate the best,
step up a gear!
- We're stuck!
- I'm talking to you!
- Don't worry, go.
- Follow a racist!
Shut your mouth!
- Bad player.
- Yeah.
- Yourself.
- Come on, it's good!
The class, Natalie!
Very classy, ​​I love it!
You're classy, ​​Natalie!
He talks about victories,
he lost against her...
- Don't react.
- ...he lost against our Jon...
- ...and there he is, cushy!
- Let her talk.
Vote against him tonight!
Do it!
- Pay no attention to it.
- Ignore her.
Julie, why this
collective hatred towards John?
'Cause everyone
thinks he's running the show,
that he plays tricks, that he lies...
- And he's a bad player!
- He talks badly to us all the time.
- He's a racist.
- When we say things
homophobic or racist,
as you did.
Don't say anything, John, let it go.
- Turn your back on them.
- Let me tell you,
you don't know him
personally.
They mention things
related to this article.
What item are you talking about?
Obviously, they know.
Do you know what they are talking about?
John is our teammate.
We support him anyway.
So you can rant
all you want.
We will support John.
Eliminate it!
Get together and eliminate him!
If you were a man,
I would kick your ass.
- Oh my God!
- Go ahead, hit me!
Hit me!
- John! Stopped!
- I'm not afraid of you!
- John, turn around!
Like the other guys in the tribe.
- I'm not afraid of you.
-John...
At this point,
why are we still arguing?
I'm ready to go back to camp.
Let's put things down, let's fight.
Good, Hunahpu, third
consecutive victory. Who wants it?
Immunity, once again
for Hunahpu.
No advice tonight.
Coyopa, third
consecutive board tonight.
Someone will be eliminated.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
It's worrying that John is
losing his patience and composure.
I think he plays
anyhow
and doing things that
won't do the tribe any favors.
It is a problem.
The ordeal was fearful.
And I might get in trouble.
Because of the guy-girl ratio.
- It was war!
- It was war.
The fact that I had
votes from the start,
then to the second tip...
I think I will have some tonight.
We need water.
Sit down, I'll get some.
- No, here we go.
- Nope.
Everyone
got high except me.
Go swimming.
They should eliminate John tonight.
Natalie is a fighter
and a loudmouth,
but for a professional athlete
like John to do that...
I found his answers despicable.
I found them rough,
mean and scary.
I didn't think I'd go through
the whole game without someone
hear about
my past talk.
Natalie called me a homophobe.
Really?
My closest ally and friend
in this tribe is a gay man.
Actions against charges.
It doesn't stick.
I will be back.
I'll put the pot
on the fire for your return.
I have made a few comments
in the past, which I regret.
I should have kept my big mouth shut .
Who knows what will happen tonight?
I could leave, the girls are aiming at me.
But I have a pretty good
strategy, which should work.
Dale is a dead weight,
useless in trials.
It is very true.
How about
making a big hit tonight
and get out Dale?
Would you be in?
Yeah.
Yeah. Anything that
can strengthen us.
Yeah, exactly.
I told them that I wanted
to eliminate Dale by surprise,
get rid of dead weight,
to turn them away from me.
But I will vote Baylor.
I think I can convince
Josh, Alec, Dale and Wes.
- I don't want to vote Dale, rather John.
- I say!
- You agree?
- Yes.
Does that bother you?
No, Baylor, that's fine with me.
- as expected for 2-3 days.
- Yeah.
- How are you?
Yeah, I...
I agree, we must act tonight.
- We're voting Baylor tonight.
- Yeah.
And in case of the unexpected, I have an idol.
Yeah.
I was a little shocked, I didn't
know he had an idol.
We want to surround ourselves with the most honest
and trustworthy,
when we start to be
so outnumbered.
And John was vague
and did things
that I disapprove of,
like yelling at the other tribe,
associating with Val and all that.
And he has an idol.
He won't use it for me.
He will use it for himself.
I go in salt water,
because of my injuries.
Sometimes we ally ourselves with people
without really knowing them,
and the more we know them, the
more we say to ourselves...
"I don't think I want to
be allied with this person,
she is the opposite of my ideas."
In John's case, unless absolutely necessary
, I don't want to use it.
I had fun with your dad.
Really? Did you find the idol?
No, she's on their side.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
And the one here? Who has it?
John told you about it?
- He told you if he brought her back?
- Yeah.
That's the thing.
Do you want to make a big hit tonight?
This is what will have to happen, okay?
To do that,
we need four votes.
You, Alec
and Baylor, you vote John.
We're eliminating John tonight.
Don't listen to what John says.
- Oh, I'm not listening!
- Ok good.
He's trying to get you
eliminated by surprise.
If the three of us
and Alec, let's all vote John,
- we eliminate John tonight.
- OK.
He shouldn't suspect anything.
Because he has an idol.
- I... I'm walking.
- And we take over, okay?
I... Thank you.
I am glad. All the votes
I know, except Dale's,
are directed to John.
- You talk to Alec.
- OK.
I hope Josh is telling the truth
and that Wes isn't lying to me.
It's weird and scary,
because you never know when...
When you're completely screwed.
What have you been told?
What about?
The vote tonight.
uh well...
You, me, Josh and Baylor,
we vote John.
We're talking about maybe firing John
while it's possible.
But physically, John is an asset.
So is it really smart?
Maybe not.
We have to make sure
he doesn't suspect anything,
- because he has an idol.
- John?
- Yeah.
- How do you know?
He told Josh.
What if he plays it?
He won't.
He thinks we all vote Baylor.
I don't see the point
of eliminating our best athlete.
Might as well take the idol with me.
I think I have laid a good foundation.
I think I handled
the right parts.
In plain sight.
But the tide
could turn, who knows?
It can be useful to have a joker.
Tonight's decision
is important.
Because if we decide
to eliminate John,
we break
the covenant of the five guys,
and we lose
the strongest of the team.
But if John doesn't leave,
what will Baylor be.
She was my first ally.
I know she is 100% with me.
John is unpredictable. I do not know.
Is there an easy vote tonight? No.
But I have to follow my instinct,
and ask me what will allow me
to go further in the game.
And I really don't know if
my decision tonight will be the right one.
John, what was the fallout
of your conversation with Jeremy
during the reward event?
He was very upset with Val leaving.
You said you tried to save her,
he said he didn't believe you.
If Jeremy and I
are still here at the merger,
I'll tell him what
I did in my tribe
to try to save his wife, but...
She bluffed so much,
I couldn't follow.
That's why she left,
not because I didn't protect her.
Wes, how does it feel
to know he was trying to save Val?
I don't like that too much.
I like to have an idea
of ​​what we are going to do, and how.
But it wasn't me
who left, so well...
Alec, what is the impact
on this tribe of animosity
what did the Hunahpu testify
to you in today's ordeal?
Because it was entirely
directed against John.
The ball wasn't
even in the back of the basket yet
that Natalie was already yelling at us.
But we can't win.
So she can throw it
at us.
What can we do?
We cannot eliminate it.
Not yet.
John, they were very specific.
They said
you were the chief of the tribe.
And that they should eliminate you,
because your elimination choices
didn't help you win.
I wouldn't say I'm the boss.
Several others do the same.
But I am blamed alone for
what five others have also done?
It's absurd.
Jaclyn, what is the effect on the tribe
to hear so many people so angry,
in a game where relationships
are central?
I think if I achieve fusion,
I now have a target on my back.
They were clearly targeting us,
Baylor and me.
"You are stupid, eliminate them.
What are you doing with this leader?"
But we're only two girls...
I do not know.
Do you think another girl
is probably going to leave tonight?
I do not know. I see
movements in the tribe.
The guys realize they
can't fire all the girls.
Maybe new alliances
are forming?
Wes, if
Jaclyn's information is correct,
it could be a big change.
She says eliminating one of them
might not be best for you.
Are you worried?
- Not really.
- Really?
With my allies, we have a plan,
and we will surely stick to it.
- Josh, are you worried?
- Nope.
Because
not everyone knows everything that's going on.
We say one thing to some
and another to others.
There are dissonances
because no one is telling
the full truth.
Baylor, what do you think the vote should produce
tonight?
For me, the most important,
it is to move away the black cloud
which covers us.
For the moment,
we follow the movement,
and you can't do that
in this game. It's hard.
Do you think the plan
you know about will come to fruition,
or will there be
votes against you?
Impossible to say with this tribe.
It's frustrating,
because no one realizes what
"being allies" really means.
So I think I
'll have votes tonight.
But Jaclyn, that would surprise you.
Because you believe it won't be
a woman, but a guy.
Yeah.
But after what I heard,
I don't know.
Maybe they've changed their minds
and are targeting Baylor.
I think we have to stick to the plan,
have balls and eliminate a guy.
And stop picking
on Baylor and me!
Wow. Well, it's time to vote.
Jaclyn, over to you.
This must be the third time
but I may finally be
sure that my alliance is stabilized.
You are negative.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
John. Equality.
Two Baylor votes, two John votes.
John.
Three votes John, two votes Baylor.
Third Person Eliminated
- Blood vs. Water...
John. That's four,
that's enough.
Bring me your torch.
Thank you Lord.
John, the tribe has spoken.
Good game.
It's time to go.
And I had a damn idol
in my pocket!
You said you had to
change things.
Maybe this successful surprise
is what this tribe
needed to turn things around.
Take your things,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
I am the kingpin of this tribe.
Count on it.
Drew wants to seize power in Hunahpu.
Basically, I'm tough.
Basically, he's a jerk.
But he is
his own worst enemy.
Ready for the next...
Jeff, one thing, before that.
No one in my tribe has
the courage to tell you about it.
I love that!
You have to believe
that the best plans
do not always succeed.
I created alliances
that I thought were solid.
I thought I was in control
and had it both ways.
And There you go.
Going out with an idol in your pocket.
I had fun and am
delighted to have had this opportunity.
And that will be a memory.