PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR
AFTER JOSH RECRUITED
JACLYN AND JOHN
THERE WAS A NEW POWER ALLIANCE
KEITH WEST ALEC AND ME.
NO ONE REALLY KNOWS YET
>> WE HAVE JOHN AND JACLYN.
JEREMY IS THE LEADER OF THE
PACK.
>> Jeff: WHEN JON WAS SENT TO
EXILE ISLAND, JACLYN'S NEW
ALLIANCE SHOWED THEIR TRUE
COLORS.
>> YOU WANT SOME FISH?
IT'S NOT A CHARITY NOW.
>> AFTER JON LEFT, I SAW SUCH A
DIFFERENCE IN THE WAY THEY
TREATED ME.
>> Jeff: AT EXILE ISLAND, JON
FOUND A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> THAT'S A GAME CHANGER.
>> Jeff: AND AT THE LAST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE-- JEREMY WINS
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
>> GOOD JOB, JEREMY.
>> Jeff: JEREMY WON SECURITY
OF HIS OWN.
>> I KNOW THAT JOSH AND HIS
MOVES WAS COMING AFTER ME.
>> Jeff: FACING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, JON AND JACLYN WERE
SECOND GUESSING THEIR NEW
ALLIANCE.
>> I DON'T LIKE THE GUYS
ANYMORE.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD GO WITH
THEM.
>> Jeff: AND IT CAME BACK TO
BITE JOSH'S ALLIANCE WHEN JON
AND JACLYN FLIPPED.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT, THE
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY, JOSH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JOSH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
10 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> MAN, THAT WAS INTENSE.
>> I'M FURIOUS THAT JOSH IS
GONE.
OUR GAME TOGETHER HAS NOW
OFFICIALLY COME TO AN END.
>>Y ALL RIGHT, MAN?
>> YEAH.
>> SO I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE WHO
TO TURN TO JUST YET, BUT RIGHT
NOW, ALL I HAVE TO DO IS WORRY
ABOUT ME NOW.
SO I NEED TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
MOVEED FOR BEING IN THE
MINORITY.
>> I KNOW, BUT THAT'S PART OF
IT.
THAT'S PART OF THE GAME.
GOOD TO HAVE YOU.
>> THE BROTHER I NEVER HAD.
>> THE THING THAT REALLY PUSHED
ME OVER THE EDGE TO JOIN THE
ALLIANCE WITH JEREMY, WAS WHEN
JACLYN FELT LIKE SHE WAS BEING
DISRESPECTED BY EVERYBODY IN THE
JOSH AND REED ALLIANCE.
I WASN'T SURE WHY, BUT MY
INSTINCTS WERE TELLING ME THAT
WAS NOT THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, I GOT
YOUR BACK.
>> IF THERE'S ANYTHING I LEARNED
FROM WATCHING PAST "SURVIVOR,"
IT'S TRUST YOUR INSTINCT.
>> YOU TWO JUMPED SHIP QUICK.
JOSH HAS BEEN LYING TO ME FOR 15
DAYS.
>> YOU HAVEN'T LINED UP.
>> MISSY HAS BEEN LYING TO ME 17
DAYS.
IT DIDN'T GO OUR WAY TONIGHT.
JON AND JACLYN FLIPPED OVER
THERE AGAIN WITH THEM, AND WE'RE
IN A BAD PLACE.
THEY CAN PICK US OFF ONE AT A
TIME.
AS SOON AS YOU STEP BACK HERE
THE COUPLES DEAL WAS OVER
BECAUSE THAT DIDN'T LAST LONG
WITH YOU.
REMEMBER THE WORD "COUPLES?
>> NOT WHEN YOU JUMPED DOWN WITH
YOUR SON LIKE THAT?
>> MY SON IS MY COUPLE.
I HAVE THE IDOL.
THE THING ABOUT THAT IS PLAYING
IT AT THE RIGHT TIME, TO MAYBE
GET ONE OF THEM OIT.
>> I THINK YOU'RE TRYING TO PIN
IT ON ME WHEN IT'S REALLY ABOUT
YOU.
>> I THINK EVERYTHING CHANGED
AFTER THE MERGE.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT ALL THAT.
MAYBE I CAN TELL THEM TO VOTE ME
OFF, THEY ALL PUT MY NAME DOWN,
I PLAY THE IDOL, I'VE HAD IT
WITH JON.
I'VE HAD IT WITH MISSY.
THAT MIGHT NOT BE A BAD IDEA.
IT'S GETTING TO CRUNCH TIME NOW.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING TO
DIVIDE INTO TEAMS.
ON MY GO YOU WILL FACE OFF ONE
ON ONE ON A WOBBLY BEAM OVER A
PIT OF MUD.
YOUR JOB-- KNOCK THE OTHER
PERSON OFF THE BEAM INTO THE
MUD.
EVERY TIME YOU DO, YOU SCORE A
POINT FOR YOUR TEAM.
FIRST TO FIVE WINS REWARD.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TEAM WILL
LEAVE HERE AND BOARD A LUXURY
FISHING YACHT, AND CREWS DOWN
COAST WHILE ENJOYING SANDWICHES,
PLUS SOFT DRINKS FOR THE
YOUNGUNS AND COCKTAILS AND
CHAMPAGNE FOR THE DAHLS.
WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'LL
CHOOSE TEAMS AND GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR TWO
TEAMS.
IT IS WES, MISSY, JON, JACLYN,
AND KEITH.
TAKING ON ALEC, BAYLOR, REED,
JEREMY, AND NATALIE.
AND RIGHT ON CUE, THE RAIN IS
FALLING.
IT'S GOING TO BE A NICE MUDDY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST MATCH-UP, GUY ON GUY.
WHO YOU GOT?
REED GOING TO GO OUT UP AGAINST
WES.
GETTING MUDDY.
GET IN.
>> LET'S GO, NATE.
>> YOU GOT THIS, DANCER BOY.
>> HEY, WES.
FOOD.
SANDWICHES.
MY FIRST FREAKING MEAL SINCE THE
MERGE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU GUYS READY?
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> COME OREED!
>> Jeff: REED GOES FOR IT, BUT
IT BACKFIRES.
WESLEY IN THE MUD FIRST.
AND REED FALL RIGHT ON TOP OF
HIM.
REED SCORES FIRST POINT.
>> ALL RIGHT, WES, IT'S ALL
GOOD.
ALL GOOD, WES.
>> Jeff: NEXT MATCH-UP, WOMEN.
WHO YOU GOING TO PUT UP?
>> YOU GO.
>> Jeff: IT IS NATALIE TAKING
ON JACLYN.
>> LET'S GO.
>> YOU GOT IT, JACLYN, LET'S GO,
GIRL.
>> COME ON, MISS U.S.A.
>> LET'S GO, BABY.
>> COME ON, JACLYN, GET IN
THERE.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS, READY?
>> LET'S GO, GIRL.
>> Jeff: JACLYN HAS THE REACH
IF SHE CAN TIEWZ TO HER
ADVANTAGE.
>> LET'S GO, JACKIE.
>> Jeff: JACLYN TRYING TO PUSH
NATALIE OFF NOW.
JACLYN GOES FOR IT.
DOESN'T WORK.
JACLYN GOES IN THE MUD FIRST.
YELLOW SCORES AND LEADS,
TWO-ZIP.
NEXT ROUND, JON TAKING ON
JEREMY.
>> HERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: BIG MATCH-UP, TWO
STRONG GUYS.
>> HERE WE GO, JON.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
JON TRYING TO REACH IN THERE
QUICKLY.
JEREMY GOES FOR IT.
JON GOES FOR IT, KNOCKS JEREMY
IN.
BLUE SCORES.
IT IS 2-1, YELLOW LEADS.
>> THERE YOU GO, BABE!
>> THERE YOU GO, JON!
>> Jeff: NEXT MATCH-UP, BAYLOR
TAKING ON HER MOM.
>> I'M SO HUNGRY.
PLEASE!
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS ?RAED GO.
BAYLOR DEFEATED HER MOM LAST
TIME THEY WERE IN A SHOWDOWN.
MOM PLOOKING FOR SOME SEVENGE.
NOW IT'S HEATING UP.
YOU GET TOO RISKY AND YOU WILL
FALL.
MISSY GOES UNDER IT.
MISSY'S OUT!
YELLOW SCORES, YELLOW LEADS,
3-1.
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
WE ARE PLAYING TO FIVE.
KEITH VERSUS ALEC.
YELLOW LEADS 3-1.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> THERE GU.
>> COME ON, CONTROL IT.
BEND YOUR KNEES.
>> BEND YOUR KNEES, ALEC.
>> KEEP YOUR CORE TIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALEC WOULD LIKE TO
PUT YELLOW IN A 4-1 LEAD RIGHT
HERE.
KEITH NEEDS TO SCORE.
KEITH REALLY CALM SHOWING
NOTHING.
HE'S BORED.
KEITH GOES FOR IT AND HE DOES
IT!
BLUE SCORES.
IT IS 3-2!
>> KEITH!
KEITH!
>> Jeff: NEXT ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
IT'S REED VERSUS WES IN A
REMATCH.
REED WON LAST TIME.
>> AAH!
>> Jeff: NICE LITTLE SLAP.
>> I CAN'T SEE.
>> COME ON.
>> Jeff: REED HAS MUD IN HIS
EYE.
THAT'S GOING TO MAKE IT TOUGH.
>> YOU GOT IT.
COME ON.
>> Jeff: REED GOES IN!
BLUE SCORES.
WE ARE TIED 3-3!
NEXT ROUND, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
JACLYN VERSUS NATALIE.
IN ANOTHER REMATCH.
>> LET'S GO, JACKIE.
>> YOU GOT THIS, JACK.
>> Jeff: JACLYN LOOKING FOR
REVENGE.
JACLYN GOES FOR IT, IT DOESN'T
WORK.
YELLOW SCORES AND LEADS, 4-3.
PLAYING TO FIVE.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
JEREMY TAKING ON JON.
IT IS 4-3, WE'RE PLAYING TO
FIVE.
>> YOU KNOW YOU WANT THOSE
SANDWICHES, JON.
>> Jeff: JON NEEDS TO TIE IT
UP RIGHT HERE.
IF HE DOESN'T, YELLOW WINS
REWARD.
>> COME OJON, GET READY.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> FEET AGAINST THE WOOD.
BALANCE, THAT'S ALL IT IS.
>> Jeff: JEREMY GOING FOR IT.
JON TRYING TO PUSH JEREMY OFF.
JEREMY FALLS IN, AND WE ARE
TIED.
4-4!
IT COMES DOWN TO ONE FINAL
MATCH.
THIS IS IT.
SHOWDOWN BETWEEN MOTHER AND
DAUGHTER.
>> LET'S GO, BAYLOR.
>> Jeff: COULDN'T BE MORE
FITTING IN "BLOOD VERSUS WATER"
TO SEE A MOTHER SP A DAUGHTER IN
THE FINAL MATCH.
>> TAKE HER OUT HERE, MISS.
>> Jeff: DOES MOM HAVE
ANYTHING LEFT IN THAT TANK?
WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUT RIGHT
NOW.
HERE WE GO.
FOR THE WIN.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THIS IS IT.
WINNER NICE REWARD, LOSERS BACK
TO CAMP.
>> KEEP IT CLOSE.
>> Jeff: WITH RICE.
>> COME OBAYLOR.
KEEP GOING.
>> Jeff: NICE BALANCE BY BOTH
WOMEN.
>> THAT'S IT, BAYLOR.
>> Jeff: MISSY JUST LOOKING
FOR THAT OPPORTUNITY.
>> WAIT IT OUT.
COME ON.
>> FINISH THIS OFF.
WATCH OUT.
BAYLOR, WATCH OUT?
>> Jeff: MISSY GOES IN.
DAUGHTER DEFEET MOM.
YELLOW WINS REWARD.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT, MISSY.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YELLOW,
NICE REWARD.
OUT ON THE WATER, SANDWICHES,
DRINKS, NICE BREAK FROM THE
GAME.
SOMETHING GOOD IN YOUR BELLY.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION ABOUT IF WE
CAN TRADE POSITIONS WITH A
MEMBER ON THEIR.
>> Jeff: YOU WANT TO GIVE UP
YOUR REWARD?
YOU CAN GIVE UP YOUR REWARD.
>> I CAN CHOOSE SOMEBODY ON THAT
TEAM AND SWITCH?
>> Jeff:YOU CAN GIVE IT TO
WHOEVER YOU WANT TO.
>> I WANT TO GIVE MY POSITION UP
FOR JON.
>> Jeff: SWITCH.
>> I WANT TO GIVE MY POSITION
UP.
>> Jeff: TO WHO?
>> TO JACK.
>> ARE YOU GUYS KIDDING ME.
>> MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: JACLYN, COME ON OVER.
JON, COME ON OVER.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, JEREMY.
>> Jeff: WOW!
CRAZY TRADE!
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I'M GOING TO CRY.
>> I'M, LIKE, HOLDING BACK TEARS
RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: JON, JACLYN, TAKE A
SPOT OVER HERE ON THE WINNING
TEAM'S PLATFORM.
JOIN THE WINNERS.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS!
>> Jeff: NATALIE, EXPLAIN THIS
TO ME.
THAT'S A MASSIVE TRADE ON DAY 22
WHEN FOOD IS SO HARD TO COME BY.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, I WAS
REALLY NERVOUS ABOUT WHAT WAS
GOING TO GO DOWN, AND WHEN
SOMEBODY SHOWS YOU THAT THEY'RE
LOYAL TO YOU, I FEEL LIKE THE
ONLY THING TO DO IS SHOW BACK
SOME LOVE AND RESPECT.
>> THANKS SO MUCH.
>> Jeff: NATALIE AND JEREMY,
IN GIVING UP YOUR SPOT, BEFORE
DECIDING ON EXILE, YOU ALSO GAVE
THE POWER TO DECIDE WHO IS GOING
TO EXILE.
IT CAN BE ANYBODY IN THIS GAME.
BUT YOU FIVE HAVE TO DECIDE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO CHOOSE JEREMY.
>> Jeff: JEREMY'S GOING TO
EXILE.
YOU GO WITH NA?
>> I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JEREMY,
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
>> JEREMY, THANK YOU SO MUCH,
DUDE.
>> Jeff: I CAN'T REMEMBER WILL
RETURN IN TIME FOR THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
TWO MINUTES AGO HE WAS ON A
YACHT.
BAYLOR, ALEC, REED, JON, JACLYN,
NICE AFTERNOON.
ENJOY IT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD DOWN TO THE BEACH.
THE BOAT WILL PICK YOU UP.
>> LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> HAVE FUN.
>> Jeff: KEITH, WES, MISSY,
NATALIE, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> WE CHOSE JEREMY TO GO TO
EXILE JUST BECAUSE I'M POSITIVE
THAT THERE IS AN IDOL ON EXILE,
AND IT WOULD BE BETTER FOR OUR
ALLIANCE TO FIND IT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
WE ENDED UP GETTING THE "W" BUT
I DECIDED I WOULD GIVE UP MY
SPOT TO JON.
>> JON NEEDS FOOD.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> I JUST WANTED TO DO THIS SO
HE KNEW I APPRECIATED HIM SIDING
WITH US LAST NIGHT AT TRIBAL.
BUT ALSO JUST TO MAKE SURE THAT
MOVINGED FOR, I COULD ALWAYS
COUNT ON JACLYN AND JON TO TRUST
ME AND JEREMY AND, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS GOING TO BE LEVERAGE FOR
ME DOWN THE ROAD.
>> HE WAS ALMOST CRYING.
>> HE WAS.
>> HIM AND JACLYN BOTH.
>> NATALIE AND JEREMY TRADED
PLACES FOR THE REWARD WAS A
BIG-TIME STRATEGIC MOVE.
I MEAN, JON AND JACKIE AIN'T
GOING TO FLIP NOW.
I CONGRATULATE HER FOR IT.
TOUCHE FOR THEM.
>> IF ME OR HE IS GOING HOME,
LET US KNOW.
I DON'T WANT TO GET BLIND SIDED.
>> I WANT TO SEND REED NEXT.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO GET
HASHTAG BLINDSIDED.
>> WESLEY WAS LETTING NAT KNOW
THAT HE DEPARTMENT WANT TO BE
BLINDDECIDED.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY TOOK THAT
HINT.
IT WAS A SMALL HINT, REALLY.
ALL RIGHT, I'M OVER IT.
>> ME, TOO.
>> ARE YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT WAY WE GET A LITTLE
HEADS UP ON PLAYING THE IDOL OR
PASSING THE IDOL BETWEEN US TWO.
>> JON AND JACLYN JOINED OUR
ALLIANCE, AND I APPRECIATE THAT.
SO GIVING UP OUR REWARD FOR
THEM, IT'S THE LEAST THAT I
COULD DO.
"THE PATH TO VICTORY IS A ROCKY
ONE.
IT'S HARD CLIMBING THE LADDER OF
SUCCESS, BUT WITH IMMUNITY IN
YOUR POCKET, YOU MIGHT FEEL A
BIT LESS STRESS."
I CAME TO EXILE BECAUSE I WANT
TO FIND THE IDOL SO I CAN
PROTECT MYSELF AND I CAN BRING
IT BACK TO MY ALLIANCE AND SAY
LOOK WHAT WE HAVE.
AND THEN NOW EVERYBODY FEELS
LIKE WE CAN TRUST HIM.
SO WHEN I MAKE A MOVE, THEY
DON'T EXPECT IT.
BUT AT FIRST, I NEED TO FIND
THIS IDOL.
THAT LOOKS LIKE THE YACHT THAT
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE ON RIGHT NOW.
EATING SANDWICHES AND DRINKING
BEER.
>> LOOK AT THAT!
>> GUYS, LOOK AT THE DOLPHIN!
( CHEERS )
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN THAT!
>> THERE THEY ARE!
>> GOING ON A YACHT, SEEING
DOLPHINS JUMP IN, IT WAS REALLY
COOL.
BEING ABLE TO SHARE THAT WITH
JACLYN WAS INCREDIBLE.
>> THESE CHIPS AAMAZING.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> IT WAS A GOOD WAY FOR JEREMY
AND NATALIE TO SHOW THEIR
GRATITUDE.
WE WERE VERY THANKFUL FOR IT.
BUT YOU DO HAVE TO REALIZE THIS
IS A SOCIAL GAME, AND THAT WAS A
VERY BIG PLAY ON THEIR PART.
TO THE BEST TEAM "SURVIVOR'S"
EVER SEEN.
CHEERS!
>> I LOVE FOOD AND I LOVE
REWARDS BUT JON AND JACLYN WERE
NOT SUPPOSED TO BE ON THE
REWARD.
>> THANK YOU, JEREMY AND
NATALIE!
>> I KNOW, THANK YOU, JEREMY AND
NATALIE.
>> NATALIE IS JUST TRYING TO
INGRAISHATE HERSELF TO EVERYONE
BY "OH, I'M GOING TO GIVE UP MY
SPOT FOR THIS.
AND I LOVE YOU, SO I'M GOING TO
GIVE UP MY SPOT FOR THAT."
IT MAKES MEANTIME TO HURL
BECAUSE IT'S SO TRANSPARENT.
YES, IT CEMENTS JON AND JACLYN
IN THE ALLIANCE BUT IN THE END
DOES IT REALLY MEAN ANYTHING?
NOT IF I CAN HELP THAT.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO LOSE
RIGHT NOW.
I MAY HAVE TO STIR UP A LITTLE
CHAOS TO STAY IN THE GAME RIGHT
NOW.
IT MAY END UP BEING THE LAST
NAIL IN MY COFFIN BUT IT'S A
RISK I'M WILLING TO TAKE AT THIS
POINT.
IT'S JUST A LONG NIGHT.
THERE'S NO SHELTER.
YOU'RE SLEEPING ON ROCKS NEXT TO
THE FIRE.
IT'S JUST NOT FUN.
I STAYED UP MOST OF THE NIGHT,
AND NOW I'M FEEL REAL LETHARGIC
THIS MORNING, LIKE I GOT HIT BY
A TRAIN.
NOT FUN.
THIS TIME I WANTED TO FIND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AND I
DIDN'T FIND IT.
LET ME GO CHECK THAT OUT ONE
MORE TIME.
I CLIMBED THIS ALL DAY
YESTERDAY, AND I CAN'T FIND IT.
THE ONLY THING I'M THINKING IS
JON ALREADY FOUND IT.
IF JON CAME OUT AND FOUND IT,
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
BUT HE SHOULD HAVE TOLD ME HE IT
AND THEN I WOULDN'T BE OUT HERE
FOR TWO DAYS YOU KNOW.
I'M DYING OVER HERE.
I'M TIRED.
I'M THINKING ABOUT WHEN JEREMY
COMES BACK, HE'S GOING TO
PROBABLY HAVE GOTTEN A MORE
SPECIFIC CLUE.
AND IF IT SAYS, LIKE, ANYTHING
ABOUT IT BEING ON THE ISLAND,
THEN HE KNOWS I FOUND THE IDOL.
>> YEAH.
>> SO EITHER PEOPLE ARE ANYTHING
TO THINK HE'S EXTREMELY STUPID
AND IS TRYING TO PULL OFF THAT
HE COULDN'T FIND IT, OR THEY'RE
GOING TO THINK I WAS LYING THIS
WHOLE TIME.
THIS IS ONE OF THOSE TIMES WHERE
I HADN'T REALLY CONSIDERED
WHAT'S GOINGS TO HAPPEN WHEN
JEREMY DOES COME BACK AND SAYS
HE CAN'T FIND THE IDOL.
THANE HE'S NOT DUMB.
MY ENTIRE COVER WOULD BE BLOWN,
AND THEN I COULD BE IN VERY BIG
TROUBLE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WE'LL NOW BRING IN JEREMY,
RETURNING FROM EXILE ISLAND.
( APPLAUSE )
WOW.
YOU LOOK BEAT UP.
EXILE KICKED YOUR BUTT?
>> IT WAS A TOUGH TWO NIGHTS, A
LOT OF BUGS.
THE CRABS WERE REAL SHAKY AND
SCARY.
TOUGH TO DO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JEREMY, TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO UNSPOOL A ROPE,
DROPPING BLOCKS INTO A BASKET.
FIRST TO GET THEIR BLOCKS
STACKED, FLAG IN THE MIDDLE,
WINS.
JUST ONE TWIST-- FOR THE FIRST
TIME EVER, IN "SURVIVOR" YOU
WILL DO THE ENTIRE CHALLENGE
USING ONLY YOUR FEET.
>> HOW DOES THAT WORK?
>> Jeff: YOU'LL USE YOUR FEET
TO UNTIE YOUR ROPE AND PUT YOUR
PUZZLE TOGETHER.
FIRST PERSON TO PLACE THEIR FLAG
WINS IMMUNITY.
SAFE FROM THE THE VOTE.
GUARANTEED A ONE IN NINE SHOT AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND BECOME THE SECOND MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
USING ONLY YOUR FEET, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO.
MAKING HISTORY, AND TRYING TO
WIN IMMUNITY TO KEEP YOUR QUEST
FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS ALIVE.
KEITH DROPS HIS PIECES.
JON, NATALIE DROP THEIR PIECES.
WES HAS HIS PIECES AND THEY GO
EVERYWHERE.
IF A PIECE DROPS AT ANY POINT,
YOU CAN PICK IT UP WITH YOUR
HAND TO PUT IT BACK IN THE
BASKET, BUT YOU'VE GOT TO USE
YOUR FEET TO DO EVERYTHING ELSE
INVOLVING THIS CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY HAS THEIR PIECES NOW.
NOW BEGINS THE LEARNING CURVE.
THIS IS NOT SOMETHING YOU
TYPICALLY PRACTICE AT HOME.
IT'S GOING TO REALLY TEST YOUR
CORE.
YOUR BALANCE.
REED OFF TO A FAST START.
KEITH DOING A NICE JOB.
JEREMY OFF TO A QUICK START.
JEREMY WON IMMUNITY LAST
CHALLENGE, WOULD LIKE TO WIN IT
AGAIN RIGHT HERE.
JON STRUGGLING.
MISSY'S MOVING SLOWLY.
>> NO PANIC.
NO PANIC.
>> Jeff: THERE ARE 21 PIECES
TOTAL, SEVEN ON THE BOTTOM,
SEVEN IN THE MIDDLE, SEVEN ON
TOP.
THEN YOU HAVE THE FLAG, WHICH
WILL HAVE TO GO UP AND OVER
EVERYTHING.
REED WORKING ON THAT SECOND
LEVEL.
GETTING A LITTLE TOUGHER NOW.
NATALIE AND BAYLOR ON THEIR
SECOND LEVEL.
WES DOING A NICE JOB.
ALEC STRUGGLING.
JEREMY ON THAT SECOND LEVEL.
KEITH MOVING VERY QUICKLY.
REED MOVING QUICKLY.
HE'S ON THE LAST PIECE OF THAT
SECOND ROW.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
REED WORKING ON THAT TOP ROW.
KEITH WORKING ON THAT TOP ROW.
IT IS KEITH AND REED.
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: YOU DON'T WANT TO PAN
NICK THIS CHALLENGE BECAUSE
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
SOMEBODY CAN KNOCK HALF THEIR
STACK OVER AND GO FROM FIRST TO
LAST, LIKE REED JUST DID.
KEITH DOING A NICE JOB ON HIS
THIRD ROW.
NATALIE NOW WORKING ON HER THIRD
ROW.
BAYLOR WORKING ON HER THIRD ROW.
JACLYN STILL MOVING SLOWLY.
MISSY TRYING TO PICK UP SOME
GROUND.
JEREMY GETTING READY TO START ON
THAT TOP ROW NOW.
WES WORKING ON THAT TOP ROW.
THE HIGHER THIS GETS, THE MORE
DIFFICULT IT GETS.
LESS WIGGLE ROOM, REQUIRES MORE
OF YOUR CORE TO LIFT THOSE
PIECES UP AND KEEP THEM STEADY.
KEITH ONLY A COUPLE OF PIECES
LEFT.
REED WITH ONLY A FEW PIECES
HUGE IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
KEITH ON THAT LAST PIECE ON THE
FINAL ROW, DISASTER.
REED ONE PIECE LEFT ON HIS TOP
STACK.
THEN IT'S ON TO THE FLAG.
REED KNOCKS ONE OFF.
HE'S GOT TO TRY IT AGAIN.
NATALIE DROPS HER STACK.
BAYLOR DOING A NICE JOB ON HER
THIRD ROW.
JEREMY TRYING TO GET BACK IN
THIS.
REED DROPS AGAIN.
GOTTA TRY IT AGAIN.
BAYLOR VERY CLOSE NOW.
>> GET IT, BAY.
COME OBAYLOR!
>> Jeff: BAYLOR NOW WITH HER
LAST PIECE ON THAT TOP ROW.
IT IS BAYLOR AND REED.
BAYLOR DROPS A PIECE.
>> GO SLOW, BAYLOR.
>> Jeff: REED TRYING TO PUT
THAT LAST PIECE, HE KNOCKS TWO
DOWN.
DOOR IS OPEN FOR BAYLOR.
BAYLOR HAS IT.
SHE'S NOW GOING FOR THE FLAG.
>> COME OBAYLOR!
>> Jeff: REED'S GOT TO PICK IT
UP NOW.
>> OKAY, CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME!
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, CAN SHE DO
IT.
>> BAYLOR, GO SLOW.
>> Jeff: YES!
BAYLOR WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY!
>> NICE!
>> YEAH!
>> THAT'S A GIRL!
( APPLAUSE )
>> HEY, HEY, NICE WORK.
NICE WORNG.
>> OH, DEAR.
>> GEEZ, HOW TOUGH IS THAT,
HUNAHPU?
>> THAT WAS INSANE.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: NICE JOB
BAYLOR SAFE FROM THE VOTE
TONIGHT, GUARANTEED A
ONE-IN-NINE SHOT AT WINNING THE
MILLION BUCKS.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 24
TOUGH DAYS IN NICARAGUA,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT,
WILL BECOME THE SECOND MEMBER OF
THE JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> ZAPPED ME.
IF I WAS 100%, THAT WOULD MAKE A
DIFFERENCE.
I ALWAYS WANT TO WIN, BUT AS
LONG AS ONE OF OUR ALLIANCE
MEMBERS WON, I'M HAPPY HOW IT
TURNED OUT.
I WAS CLOSE TO.
I'M A LITTLE BUMMED ABOUT THAT.
I FELT THAT WAS A CUSTOM-MADE
CHANCES FOR ME AND I FEEL MY
CHANCES OF BEING HERE TOMORROW
ARE PRETTY SLIM.
I MAY BE GOING HOME TONIGHT SO I
MAY LIGHT THIS CAMP ON FIRE ON
MY WAY OUT.
SO I WAS, LIKE, I WANT TO SEE
WHAT KEITH HAS IN HIS BACK BAG.
I WANT TO SEE WHAT THIS OLD COOT
IS SITTING ON.
SO I'M GOING THROUGH HIS BAG,
AND I'M LOOKING AND HE'S GOT THE
PIECE OF PAPER THAT WAS FOLDED
UP AND CREASED OVER THERE.
IT IS THE DIRECTIONS ON WHAT TO
DO WITH THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
KEITH LEFT A PAPER TRAIL.
AND I WAS LIKE IT'S A BIG ROOKIE
MISTAKE.
DON'T LEAVE STUFF IN YOUR BAG
THAT YOU DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO
FIND.
SO I DID IT.
AND I ALWAYS THOUGHT I HATE WHEN
PEOPLE GO THROUGH PEOPLE'S STUFF
BUT DESPERATE TIMES CALL FOR
DESPERATE MEASURES.
SO HERE'S THE THING, I KIND OF
STUMBLED ACROSS SOMETHING TODAY
THAT WASN'T-- IT WAS KIND OF
FORTUITOUS.
I WENT TO GRAB WHAT I THOUGHT
WAS JULIA'S BAG, AND IT WAS
KEITH'S BAG.
AND IT HAD THE CLUE TO THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IN IT.
IT'S THE NOTE THAT SAYS, "THIS
IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL."
>> SERIOUSLY.
ON A PIECE OF PAPER.
>> "IMMUNITY IDOL RULES."
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT MEANS WE KNOW WHERE THE
IDOL IS.
KEITH HAS IT.
>> I KNOW REED'S SCRAMBLING, BUT
IF KEITH REALLY HAS AN IDOL,
IT'S NOT GOOD AT ALL.
QUITE FRANKLY, IT MAY BE
SOMETHING THAT WE SHOULD THINK
ABOUT.
>> YOU GUYS STILL HAVE THE
NUMBERS AND THEN ME, BECAUSE I'M
VOTING WITH YOU GUYS.
SO I JUST WANTED TO PUT THAT OUT
THERE.
>> KEITH HAS AN IDOL?
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN IS THAT?
WHEN DID HE FIND IT?
IF WHAT REED SAYS IS TRUE,
FREAKING KEITH, OUT OF ALL
PEOPLE, HAS AN IDOL, WHICH IS
BAFFLING.
I WOULD NEVER THINK KEITH WOULD
BE THE ONE TO FIND IT.
AND BE ABLE TO HIDE IT THIS
LONG.
WHONS HOW LONG HE'S HAD IT?
SO IT'S ABOUT TO GET CRAZY.
>> SOMEBODY BROKE INTO MY BAG.
I'VE GOT THE IDOL, BUT NOW
EVERYBODY KNOWS I HAVE THE IDOL.
THE CLUE AND EVERYTHING WAS
WRAPPED UP WITH THE IDOL.
THE IDOL WAS IN MY BLUE JEANS
PANTS.
THE CLUES AND EVERYTHING WAS IN
THAT BLUE BAG.
AND IT'S NOW GONE.
>> THERE'S A THIEF OUT HERE
SOMEWHERE.
>> I MEAN, THAT'S MY STUFF.
I DON'T LIKE-- I DON'T GO
THROUGH YOUR STUFF.
I DON'T EXPECT PEOPLE TO GO
THROUGH MY STUFF, BUT DIFFERENT
PEOPLE GOT DIFFERENT VALUES, I
GUESS.
WE'RE UP-- WE'RE UP A CREEK.
SO WORD MIGHT BE OUT THAT
KEITH'S GOT THE IDOL, AND IT
MIGHT COME IN PLAY SOONER THAN
LATER.
>> KEITH HAS AN IDOL REED FOUND
IT.
>> WHAT?
>> IN HIS BAG.
HE FOUND THE PAPERS THAT SAYS,
"THIS IS AN IDOL."
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH YOURS?
>> I BURNED THEM.
>> THEY'RE DEFINITELY HIS AND HE
HAS ONE.
>> A LOT GOING ON.
TOTAL MAYHEM NOW AT CAMP.
KEITH HAS AN IDOL, SO HE'S GOT A
VERY GOOD PLAY IN HIS POCKET.
DEFINITELY COMPLICATES THINGS.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, JON GOT THAT
IDOL.
I'M TELLING YOU.
NAT, I LOOKED EVERYWHERE.
HE DEFINITELY HAS IT.
>> JON IS TRYING TO TAKE CONTROL
OF EVERYTHING.
>> YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE I TRUST
HERE,UN WHAT I MEAN?
>> YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE I 100%
TRUST.
>> DON'T TRUST NOBODY ELSE.
JON IS TRYING TO SET IT UP RIGHT
NOW.
I THINK JON HAS THE IDOL SO MY
PLAN IS I WANT TO TRY TO CATCH
HIM IN A LIE BECAUSE JON'S,
LIKE, THE WORST LIAR.
>> THIS IS THE CLUE.
I WANT YOU TO READ IT.
AND YOU TELL ME WHERE YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE ON EXILE.
>> ON THE ISLAND, RIGHT?
>> I WENT UP BOTH OF THEM.
DIGGING.
NOTHING THERE.
SO THAT'S WHY I'M, LIKE, JON HAD
TO HAVE FOUND IT.
BECAUSE I'M, LIKE, " WHY O, IF
YOU FOUND IT, WE DON'T NEED TO
GO BACK.
>> I KNOW.
>> WE COULD SEND THEM, AND THEY
COULD DIE OUT THERE.
>> JEREMY, I WOULD--
>> DANG!
HE'S GOT TO BE LYING BUT I HAVE
TO TRUST HIM A LITTLE BIT.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WE'RE TRYING TO GO TO THE FINAL
SIX, AND THEN WE'LL SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
>> SOMEBODY GOT THE IDOL.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> SENDING JEREMY TO EXILE WAS A
GREAT THING AT FIRST, BUT I
THINK RIGHT NOW JEREMY ACTUALLY
DOES BELIEVE THAT I HAVE THE
IDOL AND JUST ISN'T SAYING THAT,
SO I NEED TO DO SOMETHING AND
CHANGE THE COURSE OF THE GAME.
AFTER THINKING ABOUT IT AND
TALKING TO JACLYN, WE BOTH
REALIZED HOW MUCH WE TRUST YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> SO I-- I FOUND THE IDOL.
>> DID YOU?
>> YUP.
>> TODAY?
>> NO.
ON EXILE.
>> YES!
>> I HOPE YOU'RE NOT OFFENDED.
I WOULD LIKE JEREMY OUT THIS
TIME OR NEXT TIME, BECAUSE I'M
THINKING IF HE SAYS HE DOESN'T
HAVE THE IDOL--
>> YOU HE WILL START TELLING
PEOPLE DO YOU AND EVERYONE WILL
START GETTING--
>> YEAH.
>> I JUST GOT THIS INFORMATION
ABOUT THE IDOL, AND I'M VERY
PLEASED TO KNOW THAT JON IS
SUPER ALIGNED WITH ME.
BUT HE'S GOT THIS LOOK IN HIS
EYE.
JON IS SAYING JEREMY'S A THREAT.
JEREMY'S A THREAT.
NOW MAY BE THE TIME TO TAKE OUT
JEREMY.
I WATCH JON AND JACLYN BARREL
THROUGH PEOPLE SO FAR AND THEY
HAVE NO PROBLEM PISSING PEOPLE
OFF, AND SINCE I STARTED THIS
GAME, YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN
ALIGNED WITH JEREMY AND NATALIE
FROM MY OLD TRIBE.
JEREMY AND I INITIALLY WERE
TOGETHER FULL-FLEDGED.
SO FOR THE FIRST TIME, IT'S,
LIKE, A LITTLE BIT CLOUDY.
AND AT THE END OF THE DAY, IT'S,
LIKE, OKAY, ARE WE MAKING THE
RIGHT DECISION?
I JUST THINK MAYBE A BETTER WAY
TO DO IT IS TRY TO FLUSH THE
IDOL, TAKE TOGETHER SIX STRONG,
AND JUST BECAUSE WE ROCK THE
BOAT TOO HARD, ONE OF US IS
GOING TO FALL OUT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JOSH, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, JEREMY, HOW BIG OF A FACTOR
IS TRUST RIGHT NOW WHEN YOU HAVE
WHAT APPEARS TO BE A GROUP OF
SIX VERSUS A GROUP OF FOUR?
>> MEAN, TRUST IS HUGE.
IN THIS GAME, IT DOESN'T EVEN
HAVE TO BE SIX VERSUS FOUR.
TRUST IS HUGE WITHIN AN
ALLIANCE.
THAT'S WHAT WE'VE BEEN BUILDING
ALL SEASON.
AND HOPEFULLY, IT LASTS ALL THE
WAY TO THE END.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU DO TO
ENSURE THAT IT DOES?
>> I MEAN, IT'S LITTLE THINGS.
FOR INSTANCE, JACLYN AND JON
JOINED OUR ALLIANCE.
AFTER THE REWARD NAT AND MYSELF
WON WE GAVE DID TO THEM AND
SAID, LISTEN, YOU GUYS GO ENJOY
YOURSELF.
THIS IS THE LEAST WE COULD DO
FOR YOU HAVING TRUSTED US AND
JOINING US.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, THAT WAS A
PRETTY BIG GESTURE TO GIVE UP A
BIG REWARD TO YOU AND JON.
DOES THAT COMPLICATE THE GAME?
>> YOU KNOW, HONESTLY, IT
DOESN'T.
IT JUST REASSURED TO ME THAT
THEY'RE BOTH WITH US, AS MUCH AS
WE'RE WITH THEM.
AND THINKING BACK ON THE
DECISION WE MADE, I THINK WE
MADE THE RIGHT ONE BECAUSE IF WE
WENT WITH THE OTHER ALLIANCE I'M
NOT SURE ANYBODY WOULD HAVE DONE
THAT FOR ME AND JON.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, THEN AFTER
WINNING A REWARD, GIVING IT UP,
YOU GET SENT TO EXILE ISLAND.
>> DA-DA-DUH!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE MISTER DPIFG.
>> BUT, JEFF, IT'S NOT EXACTLY
SELFLESS.
IT DEFINITELY SERVEAISE PURPOSE.
IT CEMENTS IN TRUST.
IT'S, "HEY, YOU SCRATCH MY BARK
I'LL SCRATCH YOURSELF."
SO IT'S SELF-SERVING IN BEING
SELFLESS.
>> TRUE.
>> Jeff: WHICH IS ONE OF THE
GREATEST MOVES YOU CAN MAKE THIS
THIS GAME.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: IT'S A WIN-WIN.
>> TOTALLY.
>> Jeff: SO, JEREMY, WHAT WAS
EXILE LIKE THIS TIME.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE YOU WERE OUT
THERE A LONG TIME.
>> IN THIS GAME I'VE BEEN
FEELING ALL RIGHT, AND I'LL TELL
YOU I WAS SPENT.
SLEEPING ON ROCKS WITH NO
SHELTER.
IT KICKED MY BUTT.
I WAS EXHAUSTED WHEN I CAME
BACK.
>> Jeff: MISSY, WHEN HE CAME
BACK, DID YOU SEE THE DIFFERENCE
IN THE ENERGY?
>> OH, YEAH.
I MEAN, HE USUALLY CRUISES IN
WITH A HUGE SMILE ON HIS FACE.
AND TODAY, HE WAS COMPLETELY
FATIGUED.
HE DEFINITELY LOOKED LIKE HE HAD
BEEN IN A BATTLE.
IT WAS A DIFFERENT JEREMY.
>> Jeff: HAS THERE BEEN ANY
TALK ABOUT IDOLS, MISSY?
BECAUSE WE'RE ON DAY 24, AND WE
HAVE NOT HAD AN IDOL PLAYED YET.
>> THERE'S CERTAINLY SPECULATION
OF WHO POSSIBLY COULD HAVE IT.
BUT I THINK PEOPLE ARE REALLY
COMFORTABLE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE YOU
SHOULDN'T BE THAT COMFORTABLE IN
YOUR SKIN THIS ENTIRE GAME.
YOU SHOULDN'T.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
IT CAN SWITCH ON A DIME.
>> Jeff: JON, DO YOU THINK
SOMEBODY HERE HAS ONE?
>> I FEEL EXTREMELY CONFIDENT
THAT SOMEBODY HERE HAS ONE.
>> Jeff: WHICH, NATALIE, IF
ONE OF THOSE FOUR-- REED, KEITH,
WES, OR ALEC--
ALEC-- HAS AN IDOL, AND
THEY PLAY IT TONIGHT, THE GAME
COULD FLIP LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH, IT IS SCARY THAT MAYBE
THEY HAVE ONE.
AND, YOU KNOW, IN TURN, IT IS
KIND OF SCARY ONE OF YOUR
ALLIANCE MEMBERS ARE HIDING ONE
WITH YOU AS WELL.
>> CAN I JUST THROW SOMETHING
OUT THERE?
SO THE FOUR ON THE OTHER
ALLIANCE, TWO OF THEM, ALEC AND
REED, HAVE BEEN REALLY
FORTHCOMING IN TALKING TO ALL OF
US, BUT ON THE OTHER HAND, WES
AND KEITH HAVEN'T TALKED TO ME
OR JON ABOUT ANYTHING.
SO THAT SHOWS ME CONFIDENCE.
SO IF I WERE TO TAKE A WILD
GUESS AND SAY WHO HAS AN IDOL, I
WOULD SAY WES OR KEITH BECAUSE
THEY'RE NOT REALLY SCRAMBLING.
>> I HAVEN'T TALKED TO YOU ABOUT
STRATEGY THIS WHOLE GAME AT ALL.
AND YOU HAVEN'T CAME TO ME,
EITHER.
>> NO.
>> EITHER.
>> BUT WHEN YOU GUYS WERE TRYING
TO RECRUIT US TO BE ON YOUR
SIDE, IT PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
HELPED YOU.
>> YOU TOLD ME MY LOYALTY WITH
WAS WITH YOU.
>> I COME BACK FROM EXILE AND I
HEAR YOU'RE NOT EVEN TALKING
TO--
>> AND WHY WOULD WE JOIN YOU
GUYS WHEN YOU DON'T TAKE
CONSIDERATION OF HALF OF US.
>> SHE DIDN'T COME TO ME.
>> YOU WERE TRYING FOR US.
WHY SHOULD SHE COME TO YOU.
COULD YOU PLEASE VOTE WITH US?
BY THE WAY, WE DON'T CARE ABOUT
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
WHEN KEITH IS TALK, HE SAYS JON,
HE DOESN'T SAY JON AND JACLYN.
>> WE TRIED EARLY TORE GET THEM
COME OVER HERE, BUT ONCE JON
DECIDE--
>> WHY DON'T YOU GUYS TALK TO
THE GIRLS MORE I THINK IS WHAT
SHE'S SAYING.
>> I TALK TO YOUR MOM ALL THE
TIME.
>> HEY!
I'M A GIRL.
SHE'S A GIRL.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST DON'T GO AROUND TALKING
TO ALL THE GIRLS, I GUESS TALK
WHEN I PASS THEM OR SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: REED, GREAT NEWS FOR
YOU.
>> YAY!
>> Jeff: ANY TIME SOMEBODY IS
YELLING AT SOMEBODY ELSE AT
TRIBAL AND IT'S NOT YOU,
WHOO-HOO.
>> YOU HAVE THOSE MOMENT WHERE'S
YOU'RE LIKE KEEP GFIGHT WITH
EACH OTHER.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS WHERE
FROM SECOND TO SECOND, THINGS
CHANGE.
IF YOU CAN MAKE IT INTO THE NEXT
SECOND YOU MAY HAVE A WHOLE NEW
WORLD OF OPPORTUNITY IN FRONT OF
YOU.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, SO MUCH OF
TONIGHT'S CONVERSATION IS
CENTERED AROUND TIMING.
WHEN IS THE RIGHT TIME TO MAKE
THE RIGHT MOVE?
IS THAT SOMETHING THAT YOU THINK
ABOUT ALL THE TIME OUT HERE?
>> WHEN WE KNEW THAT JACLYN AND
JON WERE ON THE FENCE, I THOUGHT
TIMING IS EVERYTHING, ESPECIALLY
WHEN JON WAS AT EXILE.
I SAID LET ME MAKE SURE THAT
JACLYN IS ALL RIGHT.
AND PROVE THAT-- I HAVE A WIFE.
IF SOMEONE TAKES CARE OF MY
WIFE, LIKE, THAT'S ALL THAT
MATTERS TO ME.
I GOT YOUR BACK.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, WHAT HAS TO
HAPPEN TONIGHT FOR YOU?
>> WHAT HAS TO HAPPEN FOR ME IS
THAT MY ALLIANCE STICKS ON TOWER
PLAN, AND DON'T LET ANYTHING
HAPPEN THAT WILL ALLOW US TO BE
DISTRACTED FROM OUR LONG-TERM
DPOALZ, ESPECIALLY WHEN PEOPLE
ARE DESPERATE AND THEY WILL SAY
ANYTHING TO YOU TO GET WHAT THEY
WANT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
MISSY, YOU'RE UP.
>> HAPPY RETIREMENT, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTE.
IF ANYBODY HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KEITH.
REED.
KEITH.
THAT'S THREE VOTES REED, TWO
VOTES KEITH.
JEREMY.
TWO VOTES JEREMY.
THAT'S THREE VOTES JEREMY, THREE
VOTES REED, TWO VOTES KEITH.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JEREMY, THREE
VOTES REED, ONE VOTE LEFT.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
JEREMY.
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
TONIGHT'S VOTE IS BOTH A BRUTAL
AND BEAUTIFUL EXAMPLE OF WHY YOU
SHOULD NEVER GIVE UP.
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> RIGHT NOW?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: WITH JEREMY GONE,
NATALIE IS OUT FOR REVENGE.
>> I WANT TO GIVE JON A TASTE OF
HIS OWN MEDICINE.
>> AND JON BECOMES PUBLIC ENEMY
NUMBER ONE.
>> SOMEBODY FEELS COMFORTABLE.
>> HE'S GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> YOU'RE 100%.
>> I'M 100% DOWN.
>> NOW WE'RE GOING TO CHANGE THE
GAME.
>> THEY GOT ME.
THEY PULLED A FAST ONE ON ME.
I DID NOT SEE THAT ONE COMING AT
ALL.
I WAS SO FORTHCOMING WITH
EVERYTHING WITH MY ALLIANCE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE ALL SET.
IF I KNEW WE WERE GOING TO GO
LOBBY THIS, I WOULD HAVE TAKEN
THAT LAST AWARD.
I DON'T HAVE AN ALLIANCE,
OBVIOUSLY.
I'M JUST SHOCKED.
THAT'S ALL.
TOO BAD.
GOOD GUY LOST THIS TIME.