>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": SEVEN HAVE BEEN
VOTED OUT AND NO IDOLS HAVE YET
BEEN PLAYED.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
LEAVING THREE IDOLS STILL IN THE
GAME.
JON'S IDOL--
>> THAT'S A GAME CHANGER.
>> Jeff: THAT HE WITH ONLY
JACLYN AND MISSY.
>> I FOUND THE IDOL.
>> KEITH'S, THAT REED TOOK
EVERYONE ABOUT.
>> AND ONE IDOL THAT STILL LAEPT
BEEN FOUND.
>> THERE IS AN IDOL HIDDEN AT
YOUR CAMP.
>> I DIDN'T ASK HER.
SHE JUST SHOWED IT TO ME.
>> Jeff: FACING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, REED WAS THE TARGET OF
THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE.
>> MY CHANCES OF BEING HERE
TOMORROW ARE PRETTY SLIM.
>> Jeff: BUT AFTER JEREMY
BECAME SUSPICIOUS THAT HIS ALLY,
JON, HAD AN IDOL--
>> JON, YOU HAD TO HAVE FOUND
IT.
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING CHANGED.
>> I I WOULD LIKE JEREMY OUT
THIS TIME OR NEXT TIME.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
JON CONVINCED ENOUGH OF THE
TRIBE TO TAKE OUT JEREMY.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
JEREMY.
SPACING REED AND BLINDSIDING
JEREMY'S CLOSEST ALLY, NATALIE.
JEREMY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NINE ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, TRIBAL.
THAT WAS A BIGGIE TONIGHT.
REED WAS GOING HOME.
THAT'S THE LAST WORD I GOT.
I EVEN VOTED FOR REED.
>> WE ARE ALL STILL HERE BUT IT
IS ON THIN ICE, SO LET'S JUST
STAY HUMBLE AND--
>> WE NEED ONE MORE PERSON.
>> REED IS A GAMER.
HE PLAYS AND HE KNOWS HOW TO
TALK TO FOLK FOLKS AND FIGURE
OUT, MATHEMATIC NUMBERS AND ALL
THAT MESS, WHICH IS WAY ABOVE
ME.
>> AS LONG AS WE CAN STICK
TOGETHER AND NOT TURN ON WOON
ANOTHER, WE'LL FIGURE SOMETHING
OUT.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, JEREMY WENT
HOME.
IT WAS A BIG PLAY AND IT WAS A
BIG SUCCESS, WHICH WAS AWESOME.
DON'T VOTE FOR ME AGAIN AND
WE'LL FIGURE THIS OUT.
I'M TRYING TO DECIDE HOW I CAN
GO DEEPER INTO THIS GAME RIGHT
NOW, WHETHER IT'S STICKING WITH
THE JON-TYPE GROUP AND JUST
PICKING OFF SOME PEOPLE WHO ARE
IN MY ALLIANCE, OR TAKING OUT
JON.
THAT WOULD BE A REALLY GREAT
PLAY BECAUSE JON THINKS HE'S
ALPHA MALE HERE.
SO I JUST FEEL LIKE TOTALLY
BLINDSIDED.
>> I KNOW, BUT LISTEN TO ME--
>> HOW CAN I TRUST YOU GUYS NOW?
I FEEL LIKE YOU CAN'T TRUST YOU.
>> YOU WERE ALREADY OFF WITH
JEREMY.
>> TALK ABOUT A BLINDSIDE.
I HAD JEREMY AS MY PARTNER.
IT WAS REALLY HARD FOR ME BUT I
HAD TO PUT ON A GOOD FACE AND
TRY TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO
NEXT.
>> ANOTHER REASON FOR WHY THIS
HAPPENED.
>> YEAH?
>> I HAVE AN IDOL.
I FOUND IT ON EXILE.
AND I WOULDN'T HAVE SHARED THIS
INFORMATION WITH YOU UNLESS I
STILL TRUSTED YOU AND
EVERYTHING'S STILL THE EXACT
SAME.
>> IT WAS JON IN CHARGE OF THE
WHOLE BLINDSIDE, AND I WANT TO
GIVE JON A TASTE OF HIS OWN
IMMEDIATE.
I WANT TO DO IT FOR JEREMY.
IT'S JUST FIGURING OUT THE RIGHT
PLAN AND THE RIGHT MOMENT.
>> I WAS SHOWN THE IMMUNITY IDOL
CLUE WHEN WE WERE AT EXILE.
I THINK IT SAID "10 SOMETHING
FROM THE FLAG."
I HAVE TO FIND THAT BLEED IDOL.
SO TO-DO-LIST-- FIND THE IDOL.
IF I COULD PULL IT OFF, THAT
WOULD BE AMAIDSING BECAUSE I
WOULD LOVE TO GET RID OF JON.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S REWARD
CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'LL DIVIDE INTO TWO TEAMS,
CIEF INTO THE WATER, CLIMB UP A
PLATFORM, JUMP OFF THE PLATFORM
AND GRAB A KEY.
ONCE YOU'RE BACK IN THE WATER,
YOU'LL COLLECT PUZZLE PIECES AND
SWIM BACK TO THE PLATFORM AND
THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL THE
PUZZLE PIECES, YOU WILL USE THEM
TO BUILD A PUZZLE STATUE.
FIRST TEAM TO GET IT RIGHT, WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: HERE IN NICARAGUA,
BASEBALL IS THE MOST POPULAR
SPORT.
IT IS PLAY PLAYED BY KIDS ALL
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
TODAY YOU WILL SERVE AS
AMBASSADORS OF GOODWILL WHEN YOU
DELIVER BASEBALL GEAR TO KIDS
WHO LOVE THE SPORT BUT ARE IN
NEED OF SOME EQUIPMENT-- HATS,
BALLS, BAT, HELMETS, UNIFORMS--
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO PUT ON A
GREAT GAME, WHICH YOU WILL THEN
WATCH WHILE ENJOYING BASEBALL
FOOD.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: HOT DOGS, HAMBURGERS.
CARMEL CORN.
NICE LITTLE TASTE OF HOME FOR
YOU, AND A NICE WAY TO SAY THANK
YOU TO SAN JUAN DELL SOR FOR
HOSTING YOU ON THIS ADVENTURE.
WE'LL DO A SCHOOL YARD PICK FOR
TEAMS.
THAT MEANS SOMEBODY WILL NOT BE
PARTICIPATING.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE DONE OUR SCHOOL
YARD PICK.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
YELLOW, REED, ALEC, JACK LIP,
AND JON.
FOR BLEW-- MISSY, NATALIE,
BAYLOR, AND WES.
KEITH WAS NOT SELECTED, WILL NOT
PARTICIPATE IN THE CHALLENGE OR
THE REWARD.
HERE WE GO, FOR REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
WES IN THE WATER AND JON IN THE
WATER.
YOU GOTTA SWIM, CLIMB, JUMP,
SWIM SOME MORE.
GOING TO BE AN EXHAUSTING
CHALLENGE.
WES IS UP FIRST FOR BLUE.
HE'S GOT A KEY.
JON IT UP FOR YELLOW.
HE SAID GOT A KEY.
NOW YOU HAVE TO UNCLIP YOUR
PUZZLE PIECES AND SWIM THEM BACK
TO THE PLATFORM.
WES HAS THE PUZZLE PIECES FOR
BLUE.
JON HAS THEM FOR YELLOW.
WE'RE VERY CLOSE.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THE PUZZLE
PIECES UP ON THE PLATFORM, ON
YOUR MAT, ALONG YOURSELF.
WES SUP.
GO, BLUE!
>> COME OMISSY, COME ON.
>> Jeff: JON IS UP.
GO, YELLOW!
JACLYN IN THE WATER FOR YELLOW.
>> COME OMISSY!
>> Jeff: MISSY'S UP.
SHE'S GOING FOR A KEY.
MISSY HAS THE KEY.
HERE'S JACLYN.
JACLYN HAS A KEY.
NOW YOUR TRIBEMATES CAN HELP
YOU.
THEY'VE GOT A BUOY THEY CAN TOSS
OUT TO BRING YOU BACK.
MISSY SWIMMING IT BACK.
WES THROWS THE BUOY.
HE'S GOING TO PULL HER BACK IN.
A BIG HELP.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: JON GOING TO PULL
JACLYN IN.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT!
GET UP, MISSY!
ANY, BLUE!
BAYLOR IN THE WATER FOR BLUE!
>> BAYLOR!
>> Jeff: GO, YELLOW!
REED IN THE WATER FORIEL POPE
BAYLOR'S UP.
SHE'S GOING FOR A KEY.
AND SHE'S GOT IT.
REED GOING FOR A KEY BE, AND
HE'S GOT IT.
IT'S A VERY TIGHT CHALLENGE.
BAYLOR WORKING ON HER PUZZLE
PIECES.
>> GO!
PULL!
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: WE ARE NECK AND NECK.
MISSY AND WES PULLING IN BAYLOR.
SHE HAS HER PUZZLE PIECES.
REED'S UP FIRST.
GO, YELLOW!
GO, BLUE!
LAST TWO IN THE WATER, IT IS
NATALIE FOR BLUE, ALEC FOR
YELLOW.
WHO WILL COME UP FIRST?
IT'S ALEC UP FIRST.
YELLOW IS NOW IN THE LEAD.
NATALIE RIGHT BEHIND.
NATALIE HAS THE FINAL KEY.
ALEC HAS THE FINAL PIECES.
THERE'S THE BUOY.
NICE WORK BY THE YELLOW TEAM.
START WORKING ON YOUR LOCK NOW.
BLUE PULLING NATALIE IN.
SHE HAS THE FINAL PUZZLE PIECES.
START WORKING ON YOUR LOCK.
ONE OF YOUR FOUR KEYS WILL OPEN
THE LOCK.
ONCE YOU ARE THE LOCK, REMOVE
THE PLATFORM.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: YELLOW HAS THEIRS
UNLOCKED.
THEY CAN START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
BLUE STILL LOOKING FOR THE RIGHT
KEY.
>> THIS ONE.
>> CALM, CALM, CALM.
>> Jeff: YELLOW HAS THEIR
FIRST PIECE.
BLUE STILL TRYING TO UNLOCK IT?
>> IS THAT IT?
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE FOUR KEYS
WORK.
THREE DO NOT.
PANIC IS NOT YOUR FRIEND.
>> YEAH, JUST CALM DOWN.
>> THERE YOU GO, THAT'S IT,
THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: YELLOW WITH TWO
PIECES.
YELLOW WIT THEIR THIRD PIECE.
BLUE HAS TO PICK IT UP.
ANOTHER NO GO, GIVING YELLOW
MORE TIME.
>> YELLOW WITH THE FOURTH PIECE.
>> THAT'S GOT TO BE IT.
>> DON'T PANIC.
>> Jeff: FINALLY BLUE HAS IT
UNLOCKED.
START WORKING ON YOUR PUZZLE
PIECES.
YELLOW WITH ANOTHER PIECE AND
ANOTHER.
>> THAT'S NOT IT!
>> Jeff: YELLOW THINKS THEY
HAVE IT.
YELLOW WINS REWARD!
>> I LOVE YOU ALL!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BIG WIN
FOR JON, JACLYN, REED, AND ALEC.
BUT THE BIGGER STORY SEEMS TO BE
WITH NATALIE, BAYLOR, MISSY, AND
WES.
BAYLOR, THE MINUTE IT WAS OVER,
YOUR HEAD WAS DOWN LIKE YOU WERE
READY TO CRY.
>> MY MOM HASN'T WON A REWARD
YET.
IT'S JUST REALLY-- I THINK I
REALLY WANTED US TO WIN FOR HER
THE MOST.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
JON, JACLYN, REED, AND ALEC,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A NICE
AFTERNOON.
>> JEFF?
I WOULD LIKE TO GIVE THIS UP FOR
MISSY BECAUSE MISSY REALLY WANTS
TO GO ON THIS REWARD.
>> Jeff: REED, YOU'RE GOING TO
SWAP SPOTS WITH MISSY.
>> IT'S ABOUT DOING GOOD FOR
OTHER PEOPLE, AND I FEEL LIKE
THIS WOULD BE GOOD FOR MISSY.
>> Jeff: REED, COME OVER.
MISSY SWAP SPOTS.
>> HAVE FUN!
>> THANK YOU!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
>> AND WOULD YOU EAT SOMETHING?
>> YES, I WILL.
>> GO EAT SOMETHING.
>> HI.
>> BIG MOVE, REED.
>> Jeff: MISSY, YOU ARE NOT
PART OF THE WINNING TEAM WHICH
MEANS YOU, JACLYN, JON, AND ALEC
WILL DECIDE WHO GOES TO EXILE
ISLAND.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO PULL OUT OF
THIS GAME AND SEND OFF ON THEIR
OWN?
>> I HATE TO SAY IT.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LIKE
IT, BUT WES.
>> Jeff: WES, HERE'S A MAP TO
EXILE.
YOU WILL RETURN IN TIME FOR THE
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JON,
MISSY, JACLYN, ALEC, SHOULD BE A
ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME EXPERIENCE.
ENJOY IT.
REPRESENT "SURVIVOR" WELL.
HEAD OUT.
KEITH, BAYLOR, NATALIE, REED,
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
SWIM ON BACK TO SHORE.
>> MISSY REALLY WANTS TO GO ON
THIS REWARD.
IN THE GRAND SCHEME OF THINGS, I
CAN SUCK THIS UP BECAUSE WITH
THEM BEING GONE, IT WILL GIVE ME
A CHANCE TO GET THE BALL ROLLING
IN TAKING OUT JON.
>> HERE WE GO!
HERE WE GO!
BATS!
>> SO ALEC AND JON AND JACLYN,
WE ALL FOUR WALK IN TO THIS
BASEBALL FIELD, AND THESE KIDS
JUST SWARM US.
THEY WERE, LIKE, IT'S CHRISTMAS!
GIVE ME MY PRESENTS!
GIVE ME MY STOCKING!
IT WAS JUST THE SWEETEST THING
TO SEE THESE KID WITH THEIR NEW
BALLS AND THEIR NEW GLOVES AND
THEIR NEW-- I MEAN, IT WAS SO
DARLING.
LOOK, I'LL START CRYING AGAIN.
YOUR HAT!
THERE YOU GO!
WAIT, HOLD ON.
THIS IS SO FUN FOR ME.
I'VE BEEN A SINGLE MOM RAISING
TWO GIRLS FOR MOST OF MY ADULT
LIFE.
I LOVE MY KIDS, AND MY LOYALTY
TO MY KIDS IS MY NUMBER ONE
PRIERLT.
I'M GLAD THAT I HAVE THESE
CHILDREN TO KIND OF WRAP AROUND
ME, AND I NEEDED THAT RECHARGE.
I FEEL LIKE THE ENERGIZER BUNNY.
>> PLAY BALL!
>> WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
DON'T BE SHY.
>> HI!
I'M MISSY.
HI.
POPCORN!
OH, PEANUTS!
>> THIS KID REALLY WANTS SOME
ICE CREAM, RIGHT NEXT TO ME, TO
MY LEFT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I KNOW.
WANT SOME?
KIDS ARE DEFINITELY A HUGE
HEARTSTRING FOR JACLYN AND ME.
YEAH!
AS LONG AS I CAN REMEMBER, I'VE
WANTED TO ACTUALLY HAVE A KID.
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY, JACLYN'S NOT
ABLE TO HAVE CHILDREN.
JACLYN WAS BORN WITH M.R.K.H.
IT'S A SYNDROME THAT AFFECTS ONE
IN 4,000 WOMEN.
>> YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL!
>> OH!
>> WHEN JACLYN TOLD ME THAT SHE
COULDN'T HAVE KIDS IT WAS, LIKE,
OKAY, SO WE CAN ADOPT.
SO WHAT?
I'M NOT GOING TO LEAVE A WOMAN
THAT I THINK IS, LIKE, ONE OF
THE MOST INCREDIBLE PEOPLE I'VE
MET JUST BECAUSE SHE'S NOT ABLE
TO BIRTH A KID INTO THE WORLD.
>> COME ON, JON.
SHOW US WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
THE REWARD WAS A LOT MORE
IMPORTANT FOR ME AND JON THAT I
EVEN THOUGHT IT WOULD BE GOING
IN.
RIGHT HERE, JON!
JON AND I HAVE A LOT OF LOVE TO
GIVE, AND IT DOESN'T MATTER IF
IT'S AN ADOPTED CHILD.
JUST THE LOVE WE HAVE TO GIVE IS
CRAZY.
SO-- IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
>> HEY, BATTER, BATTER, BATTER,
BATTER.
>> SWEET!
>> GO, GO, GO, GO!
I GOT ON BASE, BABE.
YEAH!
>> HOME, SWEET, HOME.
>> YEP, BACK AGAIN.
>> BAYLOR, MYSELF, AND KEITH AND
NATALIE GOT BACK TO CAMP, AND I
KNEW THAT I NEEDED TO GET TO
KEITH AND HAVE KIND OF, LIKE,
THIS, LIKE, HEART-TO-HEART, COME
TO JESUS CONVERSATION SAYING
WHERE DO YOU STAND IN THIS GAME?
>> WE COULD GET THIS GOING AND
GO GET WATER AND YOU WANT TO
CHECK THE FISH NETS.
>> ME AND HIM?
>> YEAH.
>> SOMETIMES I DON'T KNOW IF
KEITH QUITE UNDERSTANDS EXACTLY
THE INTRAEXES OF HOW THIS GAME
IS PLAYED.
HERE'S THE DEAL-- THAT OTHER
ALLIANCE IS CONVINCED YOU AND
WES HAVE AN IDOL BETWEEN THE TWO
OF YOU.
WHAT THEY WANT TO DO AT THE NEXT
VOTE IS SPLIT THE VOTE BETWEEN
AND YOU WES.
SO THEY WILL THINK THEY HAVE
FOUR VOTES GOING ON ONE OF YOU
AND THREE VOTES GOING TO
ANOTHER.
>> THEY'RE INCLUDING YOU AND
ALEC?
>> YES, BUT ALEC AND I ARE GOING
TO VOTE WITH YOU AND WES.
WHAT I'M COUNTING ON RIGHT NOW
IS THAT THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE
WILL SPLIT THE VOTE BETWEEN WES
AND KEITH, BUT IF WE STAY FOUR
STRONG, WE'LL BE ABLE TO TAKE
OUT JON IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
I'M PLANNING TO GO BIG OR GO
HOME, LITERALLY, GAME RIGHT NOW.
AND I REALLY HOPE IT PANS OUT.
THAT'S-- WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> YUP, UH--
>> ARE YOU COOL WITH THAT?
>> I'M COOL WITH THAT.
THAT'S A GOOD PLAN IF WE CAN
PLAY ALL FOUR AND GET JON OUT,
THE RINGLEADER, WHICH I DON'T
CARE MUCH FOR TO BEGIN WITH.
AND I STILL WON'T HAVE TO PLAY
THE IDOL, HOPEFULLY.
>> AS LONG AS WE JUST TRUST EACH
OTHER FOR THIS ONE VOTE WE CAN
MAKE A HUGE CHANGE IN THE GAME.
>> ARE WE GOING TO TAKE ALL
THREE?
>> WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE
WE'RE GOING TO LOOK FOR THE DAMN
IDOL.
>> RIGHT NOW.
>> YES, WHEN THEY'RE GONE.
>> ARE YOU SURE THEY DON'T
ALREADY HAVE IT.
>> NO, THERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
THEY DIDN'T GET THE SECOND CLUE.
>> I'M, LIKE, READY TO GO GET
WATER.
AND NATALIE IS LIKE, "WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
WE'RE GOING TO LOOK FOR THIS
IDOL RIGHT NOW."
I WAS LIKE, "OH, SHOOT.
OKAY, LET'S GO."
IT OF.
>> IT SHOULD BE RIGHT UNDER
HERE.
>> WE THOUGHT ABOUT THE CLUE,
THE 10, BURIED, FLAG, AND OF,
ALL THE FOUR SYMBOLS THAT HAVE
BEEN IN OUR MINDS SINCE WE HAVE
BEEN AT EXILE.
>> WHY IS THIS SO BLOODY
COMPLICATED.
IF THIS ONE IS NOT FOUND, MAN,
I'M TELLING YOU-- I WENT BACK TO
THE FLAG, AND I TOOK LARGER
STEPS THIS TIME.
PAST THE CAMPFIRE, AND RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF CAMP.
WERE THESE LOGS HERE WHEN YOU
GUYS CAME?
>> YES.
>> GOOD.
IT'S, LIKE, LITERALLY THE HEART
OF OUR CAMP, BY THE FIRE.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD.
>> SHUT UP!
>> OH, MY GOD!
WE WENT BERSERK.
WE WERE, LIKE, LITERALLY OUT OF
OUR MINDS.
WE PICK UP THE POT AND RUN TO
THE WATER AS FAST AS WE HAVE
EVER DONE IN OUR LIFE.
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
OH, MY GOD!
IT'S AWESOME!
THIS IS THE IDOL.
SO SICK.
FINDING IT WAS EXACTLY HOW YOU
THINK IT WILL FEEL, YOU KNOW.
JUST LIKE YOU'RE SO ELATED, SO
EXCITED.
IT'S LIKE MY LITTLE TWINNIE,
JUST ME AND MY, YOU KNOW, FRIEND
OUT HERE.
I THINK WE KEEP MAKING JON FEEL
REALLY COMFORTABLE FOR ONE MORE
VOTE.
>> YUP.
>> ALSO REED IS VERY, VERY
SCARY.
SO WE HAVE TO ALL BE ON THE REED
PLAN.
WE GET RID OF ONE OF THE BOYS.
SO THE GUYS CAN'T TAKE US OUT
ONE BY ONE.
I WANT JON OUT BAD.
BUT WE HAVE TO GET RID OF ONE
MORE BOY BEFORE JON BECAUSE THAT
ALLOWS US TO STILL TAKE OUT JON
AND HAVE MAJORITY GIRLS.
WE GET RID OF REED FIRST.
>> WE ALL VOTE REED.
>> YES.
BAYLOR HAS BECOME MY NUMBER ONE.
MWE ARE ON THE SAME PAGE AS WE
THAT WE HAVE TO GET RID OF REED.
REED IS SO SCARY.
>> I KNOW HE IS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WE'LL NOW BRING IN WES,
RETURNING FROM EXILE ISLAND.
>> YES, WESLEY!
( APPLAUSE ).
>> DID YOU MAKE IT?
>> OH, DID I.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
BAYLOR, I'LL TAKE THE NECKLACE
BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE YOUR FEET ON A
VERY NARROW PERCH WHILE HOLDING
A HANDLE ABOVE YOUR HEAD.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU LET GO OF
THE HANDLE OR A FOOT COMES OFF
THE PERCH, YOU'RE OUT.
THE LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING
WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE
VOTE, GUARANTEED ONE IN EIGHT
SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT,
BECOME THE THIRD MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY LOOKS GOOD.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
EVERYBODY'S STATION HAS BEEN
MEASURED BASED ON YOUR HEIGHT.
SO IT IS EQUAL AND FAIR FOR
EVERYBODY.
THE ONLY THINGS YOU HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT ARE KEEPING YOUR
HANDS ON THE HANDLE AND YOUR
HEELS ON THE PERCH.
JON REALLY TEMPTING FATE,
STRETCHING WAY OUT.
>> I AIN'T FEELING IT.
I WAS JUST SHOWING OFF.
>> Jeff: LET ME SEE IF I CAN--
>> A HAMBURGER OR DONUT BURGER.
>> Jeff: TEMPT YOU DOWN WITH A
LITTLE SUGAR.
>> CANDY!
>> Jeff: IF YOU STEP OUT,
YOU'RE OUT.
>> OH, MY GOD, NO, PLEASE.
>> GUMMY BEARS.
>> Jeff: NOT INTERESTED?
>> NO.
>> Jeff: NOPE?
>> OH, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
DO BENEFICIARY THAT, JEFF?
>> Jeff: I DON'T HAVE TO DO
BETTER.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU COME DOWN.
YOU HAVE $1 MILLION ON THE LINE.
THIS IS UP TO YOU GUYS.
NOTHING, HUNAHPU?
>> CANDY?
NO.
DON'T DO IT, JEFF!
>> YOU'RE SO MEAN.
>> Jeff: IT'S TEXTURY.
IT HAS GREAT SUGAR.
>> GO AWAY!
YOU'RE SO MEAN!
>> I'M GOING TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO STEP
DOWN?
>> I'M GOING TO BE THE FIRST ONE
OUT, ANYWAY.
>> Jeff: JON IS OUT.
SORRY I TOOK RAY BITE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> EAT THAT CHOCOLATE!
>> Jeff: JON, FIRST OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE FOR A PLATE FULL OF
SUGAR.
>> OH, MY GOD, JON, I'M GOING TO
KILL YOU, I SWEAR.
>> OOOOHHH!
SUGAR!
>> ALL RIGHT, NOW, SHUT UP.
>> MY FAVORITE CANDY BAR.
I COULDN'T DO IT.
>> Jeff: JON LASTED SEVEN
MINUTES.
>> THAT'S ALL IT'S BEEN?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF HE FEELS THAT
SAFE OR NOT?
>> I WOULD HAVE STAYED UP THERE
IF I THOUGHT I WOULD BE ABLE TO
LAST.
>> HECK, I'M 53.
HOW OLD ARE YOU, JON?
>> 26.
>> 26?
ROGER THAT.
>> Jeff: WE ARE DOWN TO EIGHT.
SETTLE IN.
WE COULD BE HERE FOR A WHILE.
>> OH THIS IS HARD.
>> Jeff: IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
THERE'S NO WAY THIS DOESN'T
HURT.
>> JUST LIKE JESUS ON THE CROSS,
BABY.
HE CAN LIVE THAT LONG UP THERE,
I CAN DO IT.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF BACK
STRETCHING.
A LOT OF FEET TWITCHING.
>> OW!
>> Jeff: MISSY STEPS DOWN.
>> MOM!
>> MISSY!
>> MISSY'S DONE?
>> I'M OUT.
>> Jeff: MISSY IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
>> IT FEELS SO GOOD DOWN HERE ON
THE SAND.
>> MOM, SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
>> I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU,
SMARTY POO.
>> I HEARD IT.
>> SIMMER DOWN.
>> I'M DYING.
>> IF TWO PEOPLE STEP DOWN,
JEFF, DO THEY GOTTA SHARE IT?
>> Jeff: WOW, WES, IT'S
AMAZING WHAT YOU JUST SAID
BECAUSE I BROUGHT ENOUGH FOR
TWO.
>> I'M DOWN!
>> Jeff: WOW, BAYLOR DOESN'T
HESITATE.
JACLYN'S OUT.
>> DAMN!
>> CHOCOLATE CHIP COOKIES!
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, JACLYN JUST
GAVE UP A SHOT AT A MILLION
DOLLARS FOR FIVE CHOCOLATE CHIP
COOKIES, AND TWO GLASSES OF
MILK.
>> DAMN WASP.
>> Jeff: LET ME SEE IF I CAN
TEMPT A FEW MORE PEOPLE DOWN.
SO WE HAVE THIS NECKLACE--
>> DON'T SHOW ME STEAK.
>> Jeff: IS THAT WORTH MORE
THAN THIS?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: WES SAYS YES.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: WES IS OUT.
WES HAS A PLATE FULL OF CHICKEN
WINGS, TWO COLD BEERS.
>> THAT'S CRAZY!
>> Jeff: NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
>> CRAZY!
>> Jeff: WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
NATALIE, KEITH, ALEC, AND REED.
>> NAT, THERE'S YOUR TEAM
SITTING RIGHT OVER THERE.
>> Jeff: SO, KEITH, YOU'RE
SAYING NATALIE IS THE ONLY ONE
OF HER GROUP STILL UP THERE?
>> YEAH, IT SHOWS ME NATALIE IS
FIGHTING FOR HER TEAM AND THE
OTHER THREE OF US ARE FIGHTING
FOR OUR LIVES.
>> Jeff: SO THEN WHAT IS IT
ABOUT YOUR SON THAT MADE HIM
DROP?
>> YEAH, WES-- I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE A FOOD WEAKNESS.
I'LL HAVE A LITTLE FATHER-SON
WITH HIM AFTER WE GET THROUGH
WITH IT.
>> I ATE 58 CHICKEN NUGGETS IN
FIVE MINUTES AND WON AN EATING
CONTEST ONCE.
>> WHAT-WHAT?
>> Jeff: YOU ATE HOW MANY WHAT
AND ONE WHAT?
>> 58 CHICKEN NUGGETS IN FIVE
MINUTES.
>> Jeff: AND YOU WON THE--
>> EATING NUGGET COMPETITION.
>> Jeff: IS THAT AN ANNUAL
EVENT?
>> I NEVER HEARD OF IT.
>> I COULDN'T PASS THAT UP, MAN.
>> Jeff: I THINK WE MIKE HERE
EVEN A WHILE LONGER.
>> Jeff: KEITH'S FEET LOOK
NUMB.
THEY'RE PURPLE.
>> YOUR FEET ARE LOOKING
PURPLE,"DAD?
>> ARE THEY?
>> AAAHHH!
>> Jeff: ALEC REALLY SQUIRMING
AROUND A LOT.
KEITH STRUGGLING TO FIND SOME
SPOT THAT DOESN'T HURT.
>> I'M SHAKING.
>> Jeff: HIS WHOLE BODY IS
MOVING, AND KEITH HAS HAD
ENOUGH.
WISELY, GENTLY STEPS DOWN.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER PERSON
VULNERABLE.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE-- NATALIE,
ALEC, AND REED.
>> Jeff: ALEC IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY FOR ALEC.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO TWO-- NATALIE
AND REED.
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY ON DAY 26.
>> Jeff: THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
>> I CAN'T SPIT.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE EPISODE OF
"TWO AND A HALF MEN" WHEN YOU
WERE NAKED COOKING PANCAKES OR
SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: COOKING BACON.
>> BACON.
>> Jeff: THAT WAS FUN.
>> THAT WAS AWESOME, DUDE.
I LOVE THAT SHOW.
>> IS ANY MORE FOOD COMING OUT
OR NO?
>> Jeff: YOU'RE TELLING ME
AFTER THREE HOURS OF BATTLING
FOR IMMUNITY, NOW YOU WOULD TAKE
SOME FOOD AND STEP DOWN?
>> HE DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HE'S
GOING TO COME DOWN.
IF I'M GOING TO COME DOWN, IT'S
GOING TO BE FOR SOME FOOD, NOT
FOR ANYTHING ELSE.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> ALL RIGHT, PITA?
SOME WINGS.
ONE COOKIE, I'M GOOD.
AND AND JUST A GLASS OF WATER,
SOME ICE WATER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE HILARIOUS.
>> Jeff: SO HERE'S THE PIZZA,
CHICKEN WINGS, COOKIE, WATER,
BEER.
AND HERE'S THE NECKLACE.
JUST BECAUSE YOU ASKED FOR IT
DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE TO TAKE
IT.
IT IS STILL YOUR DECISION.
>> OH, GEEZ!
>> YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
IF I'M GOING TO FALL OUT AFTER
THREE HOURS I MIGHT AS WELL EAT
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW.
>> Jeff: UP TO YOU, NATALIE.
NATALIE STEPS OUT AND
IMMEDIATELY CRUMBLES.
>> AM I SET?
>> Jeff: REED WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
( APPLAUSE )
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: NEITHER PLAYER CAN
MOVE.
NATALIE CAN TASTE THE FOOD.
SHE JUST CAN'T GET TO IT.
REED'S ABOUT TO GET A NECKLACE
IF HE CAN STAND UP.
WHAT AN ENDING TO A LONG
ENDURANCE CHALLENGE.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THAT IS HOW YOU DO
IT.
>> DO YOU SEE THIS FOOL?
>> "DO YOU SEE THIS FOOL?"
>> WHEN I STARTED CLOSING MY
EYES AND SEEING STARS AND I FELT
LIKE I WAS GOING TO THROW UP I
KNEW I WAS GOING TO GO OUT SO I
FIGURED I MIGHT AS WELL GET SOME
SUSTENANCE IN MY BODY AND I'M
GOING TO LOSE.
>> JEFF!
>> Jeff: REED.
>> IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE.
>> Jeff: INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AFTER 26 DAYS, ONE YOU GO HOME
TONIGHT.
YOU'LL BECOME THE THIRD MEMBER
OF THE JURY-- IT WON'T BE YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
GET UP WHEN YOU CAN.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD JOB, REED.
>> AT LEAST I'M NOT GOING HOME
TONIGHT BECAUSE I WILL NOT BE
GIVING UP THIS IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
AND HOPEFULLY I CAN RALLY PEOPLE
AROUND TO VOTE JON TONIGHT, AND
I AM, LIKE, EEWWW!
>> NATALIE, REED, WHATEVER.
>> REED, HOW MUCH MORE DID YOU
HAVE IN YOU, REALLY?
>> A WHILE.
>> JON STEPPED DOWN SEVEN MINUTE
INTO THE CHALLENGE TODAY.
IT'S ALWAYS VERY TELLING WHEN
PEOPLE STEP DOWN, WHEN THEY FEEL
LIKE THEY DON'T HAVE TO TRY, AND
WHO ENDS UP STEPPING DOWN FIRST.
SO I WAS LIKE, FINE.
THAT MEANS HE'S GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> JON?
>> YES.
>> BASICALLY, HOW THIS WORKS IS
I'M GOING TO TRY TO MAKE THE
MAJORITY ALLIANCE HAVE FOUR
PEOPLE VOTE FOR KEITH AND THEN
TO HAVE THREE MORE PEOPLE VOTE
FOR WES.
THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE THINKS IS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
BUT BASICALLY, MYSELF, WES, ALEC
AND KEITH VOTE FOUR STRONG, AND
WE WOULD BE SENDING JON HOME
TONIGHT.
IT'S AN AMAZING PLAN, BUT IT HAS
TO BE STUCK TO.
>> JUST MAKE SURE YOU VOTE FOR
JON TONIGHT.
>> THINK IT WILL WORK?
>> YEAH, JUST MAKE SURE YOU VOTE
FOR JON.
AND I'M GONNA SAY I WANT YOU AND
BAYLOR AND MISSY AND NAT TO VOTE
FOR KEITH.
BUT WE'RE REALLY VOTING FOR JON.
>> I KNOW.
>> ARE YOU DOWN?
>> I'M DOWN.
WE CAN MAKE THIS HAPPEN.
WE CAN TURN THIS GAME.
>> I'M DOWN.
>> WHY DON'T YOU AND HER AND HIM
AND NAT VOTE FOR KEITH?
AND THEN JON, JAC, AND I WILL
COWEST.
>> DO YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH
THAT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> COOL.
>> THE OPPOSING ALLIANCE THINK
REED AND I ARE GOING TO VOTE
WITH THEM TONIGHT AGAINST WES
AND KEITH, BUT WHAT WE ARE GOING
TO DO IS WE'RE GOING TO BLINDED
SIDE JON TONIGHT.
>> LET ME JUST TELL YOU WHAT
JUST HAPPENED.
>> YEAH, HE JUST CAME UP TO ME
AND SAID ARE WE STILL DOING THE
SPLIT.
WE NEED TO SPLIT THE KEITH AND
WESLEY THING.
I KNOW.
LISTEN, IF WE DON'T DO THIS NOW,
WES OR KEITH IS GOING TO SCOOT
ON UP WITH AN IDOL.
ONE OF THEM HAS IT.
>> REED IS NOT GOING TO VOTE
WITH US TONIGHT.
>> ALEC AND REED ARE STILL, YOU
KNOW, REALLY TRYING TO BE IN
WITH US.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE IN WITH
KEITH AND WESLEY.
I WILL BET YOU HE WILL VOTE WITH
US TONIGHT.
>> HOW WE DOING, DUDE?
>> WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
THE SPLIT.
>> YOU REALLY DOWN?
>> YEAH, I'M DOWN.
I'M DOWN.
>> WE'VE GOT IT.
>> HE'S VOTING KEITH.
>> YOU'RE 100%.
>> I'M 100% DOWN, YEAH.
>> THIS IS IT.
>> THIS IS, LIKE, WHERE WE BUILD
TRUST RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH, I GOTTA.
LET'S DO IT.
>> TONIGHT'S TRIBAL IS THE FIRST
TRIBAL THAT I AM NOT REALLY
CALLING THE SHOTS.
SO IT IS THE FIRST TIME THAT I
AM AT THE MERCY OF MY ALLIANCE.
I'M SAVING THE IDOL FOR EITHER
JACLYN OR ME.
WHOEVER MAKES IT FARTHEST.
I FEEL LIKE IT WOULD BE SELFISH
TO TIEWZ ON MYSELF RIGHT NOW.
THE ONLY THING THAT GIVES ME A
LITTLE HOPE GOING INTO TONIGHT
IS THE REASSURANCE I HAD TALKING
WITH ALEC, AND THAT IS WHY I
BELIEVE THAT TONIGHT WILL GO AS
PLANNED.
THIS TRIBAL IS DEFINITELY THE
MOST IMPORTANT TRIEBLG SO FAR.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JOSH AND JEREMY, VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, JACLYN, THE LAST TWO TRIBAL
COUNCILS, TWO PEOPLE WHO HAD A
SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME HAVE
BEEN BLINDSIDED.
WHERE'S YOUR HEAD NOW?
>> I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I'M IN THE FIVE STRONG
RIGHT NOW, BUT WHO KNOWS?
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, THE TRICKY
THING IS YOU CAN'T HELP BUT
THINK, OKAY, I KNOW I TRUST
THESE PEOPLE BUT SO DID JOSH AND
SO DID JEREMY.
>> YEAH, TRUST IS REALLY
DIFFICULT IN THIS GAME BECAUSE
SOMEBODY SAYS I 100% AM WITH YOU
DOESN'T MEAN THAT THEY ARE EVER.
>> Jeff: KEITH, WITH ALL THIS
TALK ABOUT TRUST, NOT A SINGLE
IDOL HAS BEEN PLAYED YET THIS
SEASON.
>> SOMEBODY FEELS COMFORTABLE.
THAT'S ALL I CAN FIGURE OUT.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, IT'S TRICKY
BECAUSE YOU'RE ROLLING THE DICE.
YOU'RE THINKING I'LL USE THIS
NEXT TRIBAL OR THE ONE AFTER,
BUT YOU CAN'T GET TO THE END IF
YOU DON'T SURVIVE EVERY SINGLE
TRIBAL.
>> YEAH, AND IF I EVER HAVE AN
IDOL, IT WILL FEEL LIKE A
TBLESSING AND A CURSE ALL IN ONE
BECAUSE YOU HAVE THIS PRESSURE
TO USE IT AT THE PERFECT TIME.
AND IT IS ALL ABOUT TIMING IN
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: REED, NATALIE SAID AN
IDOL CAN BE A BLESSING OR A
CURSE BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT IT
TO BE A SOUVENIR.
>> SURE.
AND LOOKING AT THE CHALLENGE,
YOU HAD FIVE PEOPLE THAT DID
STEP DOWN THAT CLEARLY FELT VERY
COMFORTABLE.
BUT IT WAS INTERESTING WHEN WES
STEPPED DOWN BECAUSE HE WASN'T
NECESSARILY IN THAT GROUP OF
PEOPLE.
SO IT MAKES YOU WONDER THEN DO
WES AND KEITH HAVE AN IDOL?
ARE THEY SHARING IT, OR WHAT
REALLY IS HAPPENING HERE?
>> Jeff: KEITH, IT DOESN'T GET
REQUEST MORE DIRECT THAN THAT.
>> IT DOESN'T.
YOU'RE EXACTLY RIGHT.
SO HUE EASY THAT WAS.
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN, IT'S
BAM!
IDOLS ARE EVERYWHERE.
I SAY STICK TO THE PLAN.
YOU KNOW, AT THIS POINT, THAT'S
ALL I CAN SAY.
>> Jeff: WOW, JON, STICK TO
THE PLAN.
>> THIS IS THE MOST CONFUSING
THING.
YOU THINK YOU HAVE A PLAN.
MAYBE SOME PEOPLE ARE IN ON IT,
MAYBE SOME PEOPLE AREN'T.
IT'S A BOMBSHELL.
>> JUST KEEP THE SAME.
WE'LL GO WITH YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> NO?
OKAY.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: MISSY, THIS IS
FANTASTIC TO WATCH BUT NOT WHAT
YOU WANT IF YOU ARE ONE OF THE
NINE PLAYERS HERE.
>> NO, YOU DON'T WANT THIS AT
ALL.
THIS IS, LIKE, COMPLETE CHAOS.
AND IT'S LIKE POPCORN.
LOOK WHAT'S HAPPENING.
'M TALKIN TALKING AND THEY'RE
POPPING.
>> BAYLOR, WHAT DOES YOUR GUT DO
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE YOU HAVE SO
MANY STORIES GOING EVERYWHERE,
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT'S REAL AND
WHAT ISN'T.
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU'RE
AT, LIKE, A FAIR AND YOU'RE
LOOKING IN THOSE DISTORTED
MIRRORS, OKAY, WELL, I FEEL LIKE
ALL THREE OF THEM ARE JUMBLED UP
AND I'M REALLY FAT, REALLY
SKINNY AND LIKE THIS RIGHT NOW.
AND I THINK EVERYBODY MIEFL LIKE
THAT.
>> Jeff: THAT'S A GOOD
ANALOGY.
>> IT IS.
>> Jeff: PRETTY GOOD.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN I THINK UNTIL THE MOMENT
I GET TO THE VOTING TONIGHT IS
WHEN MY GUT WILL TELL ME WHAT TO
DO BECAUSE THE CONVERSATIONS
THAT ARE BEING HAD, THAT'S NEVER
HAPPENED BEFORE, AND I FEEL LIKE
WE MAY HAVE NOT AS BEEN AS CLOSE
OR ORGANIZED AS WE THOUGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
>> WE'RE STILL DOING THIS.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: REED, YOU'R YOU'RE UP.
HE'S STILL TALKING.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> DUDE, PLAY YOUR IDOL.
>> WHAT.
>> PLAY YOUR IDOL.
>> REALLY?
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> UP TO YOU.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> JEFF.
I'D RATHER PLAY THIS THAN GO
HOME WITH IT IN MY POCKET.
>> YEAH, PULL IT OUT.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTE CAST FOR JON WILL NOT
COUNT.
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> YOU WANT TO PLAY IT, YOU PLAY
IT.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> HAVEN'T EVEN OPENED IT.
>> Jeff: HOW DO YOU KNOW IT'S
REAL?
>> AH, JUST TAKING A CHANCE.
>> Jeff: THIS, TOO, IS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR KEITH WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JON.
DOES NOT COUNT.
JON.
KEITH.
DOES NOT COUNT.
KEITH, DOES NOT COUNT.
JON, DOES NOT COUNT.
>> I'M SO GLAD I PLAYED THAT.
>> KEITH, NOBODY WITH ANY VOTES.
WES.
THAT'S ONE VOTE WES, ONE VOTE
LEFT.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
WES, YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
>> SLY DOG YOU.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: WES, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> DAMN, DAMN, DAMN.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT'S QUITE
CLEAR THAT YOU GUYS TRULY ARE
PLAYING THIS GAME IN THE MOMENT.
IT'S AGGRESSIVE, AND IT'S RISKY.
AND NOW THAT YOU'VE STARTED, YOU
CAN NEVER GO BACK.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON A
SURVIVOR
TENSIONS ARE HIGH.
>> BAYLOR, YOU'RE A BRAT.
>> SHUT YOUR MOUTH FOR A SECOND
AND LISTEN.
>> ONE FIGHT WILL CHANGE THE
GAME FOR GOOD.
>> DON'T TOUCH ME.
>> WE HAVE TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT AND SHE WON'T TALK TO
ME.
NOT A GOOD TIME TO DO THAT.
>> SCREW HIM.
>> I HOPE MY DAD GETS FAR AND I
HOPE HE GETS TO THE FINAL THREE
AND WINS A MILLION BUCKS.
THIS IS THE EXPERIENCE OF A
LIFETIME AND I I AM GLAD I GOT
TO EXPERIENCE IT WITH HIM.
THOSE WINGS WERE NOT WORTH $1
MILLION.
I DO REGRET THAT DECISION
STEPPING OFF BUT, YOU KNOW, YOU
HAVE TO WING IT SOMETIMES AND
TAKE RISKS AND YOU HAVE TO RISK
IT TO GET THE BISCUIT.