>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": SAY YOUR GOOD-BYES.
THIS GAME IS ON.
SINCE DAY ONE, BLOOD VERSUS
WATER HAS BEEN A TALE OF TWO
TRIBES HEADING IN OPPOSITE
DIRECTIONS.
HUNAHPU WINS!
COYOPA COULDN'T WAYNE CHALLENGE.
HUNAHPU WINS IMMUNITY FOR THE
THIRD STRAIGHT TIME.
AND THEY WEREN'T GETTING ALONG.
>> BAYLOR, YOU TOLD ME TO VOTE
DALE, YOU DID.
OWN IT!
>> Jeff: THERE IS CLEARLY
TENSION IN THIS TRIBE.
HUNAHPU WAS UNBEATEN.
>> WOOO!
>> Jeff: AND LIVING LIKE
KINGS.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: BUT EVEN THEY
COULDN'T LIVE IN PEACE.
>> JEREMY'S GOT AN IDOL.
KEEP THAT IN MIND.
>> KEITH IS TRYING TO GET ME
OIT.
WE NEED TO HAVE EACH OTHER'S
BACKS.
WE NEED TO GO TO TRIBAL AND GET
SOME OF THE SNAKES THAT ARE ON
OUR TEAM OFF.
>> Jeff: AND DREW DECIDED TO
THROW THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
DREW MISSES AGAIN.
HUNAHPU WINS THEIR FIRST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE!
BUT AT TRIBAL COUNCILS HAD PLAN
BACKFIRED AS A MAJORITY CAME
TOGETHER TO BLINDSIDE DREW.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VERSUS WATER,"
LAEG HIS LONE ALLY JON.
>> GOOD PLAY.
>> Jeff: 14 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
>> THAT WAS A NARLY TRIBAL.
>> WHAT A LEARNING EXPERIENCE.
>> TRIBAL WAS FREAKING INSANE.
>> I WAS DEFINITELY ONE OF THE
ODD ONES OUT.
THAT WAS FUN.
DREW WAS DEFINITELY A FRIEND OF
MINE.
BUT HE STEPPED ON A LOT OF
PEOPLE'S TOES WILL THE PAST FEW
DAYS, SO I AM VERY NERVOUS, AND
I'VE GOT A LOT OF DAMAGE CONTROL
TO DO.
IF YOU GUYS WOULD HAVE SAID IT
TO ME I WOULD HAVE BEEN RIGHT ON
BOARD WITH IT.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> HE SAID, "YOU'RE EITHER WITH
ME OR AGAINST ME AND IF YOU'RE
NOT, YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
( BLEEP ) IS GOING ON HERE."
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> JON, YOU'LL BE MUCH BETTER
OFF IN THIS TRIBE WITHOUT HIM.
>> I THINK YOU WILL.
>> JON IS ON HIS APOLOGY TOUR
BECAUSE HE KNOWS HE'LL BE GONE
NEXT.
>> I SHOULD HAVE BEEN RIGHT
THERE FOR YOU.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN LIKE, YES,
ABSOLUTELY, THE WAY YOU THINK IT
IS, ABSOLUTELY, I'M DOING IT.
AND I DIDN'T DO THAT I'M & I'M
TRYING TO APOLOGIZE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HE COMES TO ME.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING.
I JUST SWOOPED HIM UP.
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
>> THIS IS ME TRYING TO MAKE
SURE THAT YOU REALIZE I'M STILL
HERE FOR YOU.
>> I'M RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
WHERE I WANT TO BE.
THIS IS PERFECT, I'M IN A
BEAUTIFUL SPOT RIGHT NOW.
>> TREE MAIL.
>> YEAH!
>> READ IT, WES.
>> CAN THE ARE YOU TIRED OF THE
LONG TRIP TO THE ARENA?"
>> OH, NO.
>> "ARE YOU TIRED OF BATTLING
LOVED ONES?
GET READY TO GET TIRED.
IT'S TIME TO GET BACK TO THE
ARENA."
>> THE GOOD THING SWE'RE THE
FIRST ONES IN THIS MORNING.
AND THEY GOT TO DO THE WALK OF
SHAME RIGHT IN FRONT OF US.
>> SOMEONE COMING BACK INTO THE
ARENA WITH ONE LESS PERSON, THE
WALK OF SHAME.
SINCE WE WON IMMUNITY, IT'S
GOING TO BE NICE TO HAVE THE
OTHER TEAM DO IT, EXCEPT IF IT'S
YOUR LOVED ONE WHO IS NOT THERE.
>> THEY ALSO WANT TO KEEP
WINNING CHALLENGES.
>> THEY WANT TO KEEP WINNING.
>> THERE'S ANOTHER SHOWDOWN IN
THE ARENA, AND I WILL ABSOLUTELY
BE EXCITED TO FACE OFF AGAINST
TRUE DROOU.
HE SOCKED ME IN THE MOUTH A
COUPLE OF TIMES ALREADY, BUT I'M
STILL STANDING AND IF I CAN SOCK
HIM AND KNOCK HIM DOWN, I'M
GONNA.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
COYOPA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW HUNAHPU TRIBE.
DREW VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> OH, MY GOD!
A LOT OF SHOCKED FACES, SOME
EMOTION.
ALEC, LET'S START WITH YOU.
YOUR BRO IS GONE.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T GET IT.
I THINK DREW IS ONE OF THE BEST
PLAYERS THEY HAD OVER THERE.
MAYBE THEY SAW HIM AS A BIG
THREAT.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN IT.
CLEARLY, THAT WAS IT.
WHAT ELSE COULD IT HAVE BEEN,
GUYS?
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, YOU LOOK
SHOCKED.
WHY ARE YOU SHOCKED?
>> I MEAN, I THOUGHT DREW WAS
MR. POPULAR, LIKE, YOU KNOW--
( LAUGHING )
REALLY GOOD AT EVERY CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: JOSH, I'M SHOCKED
THAT ANYBODY'S SHOCKED WHEN
SOMEONE FROM THE OTHER TRIBE
MAKES THE DECISION BECAUSE YOU
HAVE NO INFORMATION.
>> THAT'S THE THING.
I MEAN, WE WERE ALL TRYING TO
SPECULATE WHO WE THOUGHT WOULD
GO HOME, BUT THE TRUTH, IS WE'RE
NOT IN THEIR TRIBE SO WE DON'T
KNOW THE TRIBE DYNAMIC, AND IT
SUCKS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
READY FOR ANOTHER SHOCK.
EVERYBODY, DROP YOUR BUFFS.
>> OH, BABY!
>> I KNEW IT!
>> SON OF A GUN.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY, DROP YOUR
BUFFS.
WE ARE SWITCHING TRIBES.
>> OH, BABY.
>> SON OF A GUN.
>> I KNEW IT!
>> Jeff: KELLEY, WOULD YOU BE
EXCITED IF YOU GOT PAIRED UP
WITH YOUR DAD?
>> GOSH, THAT'S SO TOUGH.
I MEAN, WE ALL CAME OUT HERE
WANTING TO PLAY WITH OUR LOVED
ONES, BUT I THINK THE PEOPLE
THAT DON'T HAVE LOVED ONES RIGHT
NOW ALMOST FEEL A LITTLE BIT
FREE, AND THE PEOPLE WITH LOVED
ONES ARE ALMOST LOOKED AT AS
TARGETS RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, DO YOU AGREE
WITH KELLEY, IN SOME WAYS HAVING
VAL GONE SORT OF GIVES YOU A
LITTLE MORE FREEDOM?
>> WHEN YOU'RE IN A PAIR, THAT'S
DANGEROUS.
BUT I MEAN 32 ?OGHT I WOULDN'T
GIVE TO HAVE VAL ON THE OTHER
SIDE RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: JOSH WHAT, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO SEE HAPPEN?
>> AT THIS POINT, I ALMOST DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHAT I WANT TO HAPPEN
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, YOU GET CLOSE
TO YOUR TRIBE.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU'RE LIKE,
OH, WAIT.
I MIGHT ACTUALLY PLAY WITH MY
LOVED ONE.
I DON'T KNOW!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE
FIGURE THIS OUT?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: LET'S DO THIS.
>> MY STOMACH HURTS.
>> Jeff: GRAB ONE, PASS IT
AROUND.
THE GAME IS ABOUT TO CHANGE.
ALL RIGHT, OPEN UP.
LET'S SEE WHO'S GOING TO BE WITH
WHO.
KELLEY GOING TO BE HOOKED UP
WITH HER DAD.
MISSY GOING TO BE HOOKED UP WITH
HER DAUGHTER.
IF YOU HAVE BLUE, COME ON OVER
HERE.
IF YOU HAVE ORANGE, DOWN HERE.
>> FIRST OF ALL, GIVE ME A HUG!
I'VE MISSED YOU.
>> Jeff: JOSH IS SWITCHING
TRIBES.
>> HI, BABY.
>> JON GOING TO BE HOOKED UP
WITH HIS GIRLFRIEND.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: WE'LL HAVE TWO
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT TRIBES.
ON COYOPA, WE HAVE THREE PAIRS
OF LOVED ONES TOGETHER-- KELLEY
AND HER DAD, DALE.
MISSY AND HER DECATUR BAYLOR.
JACLYN AND HER BOYFRIEND, JON.
AND ONE LONE PERSON IN KEITH.
ON HUNAHPU COMPLETELY OPPOSITE.
WE HAVE ONE PAIR OF LOVED ONES,
JOSH AND REED-- WITH A BUNCH OF
SINGLES -- WES, ALEC, JEREMY,
JEWEL EXE NATALIE.
KEITH, HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
YOU'RE THE LONE SINGLE ON THAT
TRIBE?
>> I KNOW.
THAT'S NOT GOOD, JEFF.
I MEAN, I WISH I WOULD HAVE BEEN
WITH WESLEY, YOU KNOW, TALK A
LITTLE BIT.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM IN 11 DAYS.
BUT I GUESS WE'LL DO OKAY.
I MEAN--
>> YEAH, WE WILL.
>> LIKE THEY SAID EARLIER,
THOUGH, SINGLES ARE KIND OF A
TARGET NOW SINCE I'M WITH THREE
PAIRS.
>> Jeff: JOSH, REED, YOU'RE
THE ONLY COUPLE OVER HERE.
REED, DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU MIGHT
BE A ATTACKER NOW BECAUSE YOU
COULD REPRESENT TWO VOTES?
>> I'D LIKE TO HOPE NOT, BUT, I
MEAN, IT ALWAYS-- YEAH, THE
POSSIBILITY IS DEFINITELY THERE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TWO NEW
TRIBES, 11 DAYS IN IN, THE GAME
HAS CHANGED ONCE AGAIN.
COYOPA, HUNAHPU, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GET TO KNOW YOUR NEW
TRIBEMATES.
>> COYOPA NOW, HUNAHPU?
COYOPA NOW!
>> WHEN I FIRST REALIZED THAT
JACLYN AND I WERE GOING TO BE ON
THE SAME TRIBE, IT WAS AN
EXTREMELY HAPPY MOMENT RIGHT
WHEN I NEEDED IT.
WHEN I WAS AT HUNAHPU, I WAS ON
THE WRONG SIDE OF THE NUMBERS,
SO THE TRIBE SWAP CAME AT THE
RIGHT TIME.
IT'S A WHOLE GAME CHANGER.
>> WELCOME HOME!
>> THIS IS OUR PLACE.
>> NICE.
>> MI CASA SU CASA.
>> OURS IS PROBABLY AT LEAST
DOUBLE THIS SIZE.
>> OUR BEACH IS PRETTY BUT WE
HAVE NO FOOD.
>> WE HAVE PLENTY OF FOOD OVER
THERE.
>> WE DON'T HAVE NOTHING.
>> NOTHING?
>> THERE'S, LIKE, BARELY TWO
SCOOPS.
>> TWICE A DAY, BUT VERY SMALL
PORTIONS PURPOSE.
>> WE WERE GOING OUT OF CONTROL
AT THE START, OBVIOUSLY.
WE STARTED OFF AND THEN WE JUST
FORGOT ABOUT RATIONING.
>> WE STARTED WITH JUST ONE
PORTION A DAY.
WE JUST DID ONE A DAY.
AND IT WAS SMALL.
WE DID A SMALL ONE A DAY.
>> I'D SAY THERE ARE TWO OF
THESE, AND THAT'S IT.
>> YOU COME TO A NEW TRIBE, A
NEW CAMP, AND IT SUCKS KIND OF,
BECAUSE THE FOOD SITUATION ON
THIS CAMP IS HOOCIAL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY WERE
THINKING, THINKING THEY'VE GOT
THIS MUCH RICE LEFT, AND THEY
GOT ANOTHER 20-SOMETHING DAYS.
WE PROBABLY HAD MORE THAN HALF A
BAG, AND THEY GOT A HAND FULL OF
RICE LEFT.
IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN WHY THEY
WERE WINNING.
>> I'M BUMMED.
>> BUT, WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
>> WE EAT RICE, BEANS, AND
SNAILS.
THIS MORNING I WASN'T ON
ANYONE'S RADAR AND I COULD DO
WHATEVER I WANTED.
AND WHAT HAPPENS?
MY WORST NIGHTMARE-- A TRIBE
SWAP.
WE GET WES AND ALEC AND JOSH
TOGETHER ON OUR TRIBE.
>> HI!
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> AAAHH!
>> SO ALL THEY HAVE TO DO IS
JOSH WORK HIS MAGIC ON REED, AND
REED COULD JUMP SHIP.
AND MY GAME IS SHFT.
THEY'RE GOING TO GO RIGHT AFTER
ME, I GUARANTEE THAT.
>> I WAS HOPING THAT MAYBE THERE
WOULD BE, LIKE, SOMETHING BACK
HERE, NEW TRIBE!
HERE'S A STEAK!
I'M SO EXCITED ABOUT THE SWITCH,
AND I WAS EXCITED TO ACTUALLY
GET TO PLAY WITH REED.
I'VE BEEN WONDER WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH HIM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE GET TO DO
THIS.
>> IT'S AMAZING.
>> MY RELATIONSHIP WITH REED
DEFINITELY GAVE ME THE STRENGTH
TO COME OUT TO MY FAMILY AND TO
MY FRIENDS.
I GREW UP A VERY CONSERVATIVE
CHRISTIAN.
MY DAD WAS A PASTOR, AND SO NOT
EVERYONE AGREES WITH HOW I'M
LIVING MY LIFE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE WALKING
ON THE BEACH TOGETHER.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S AMAZING.
>> WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER TWO YEARS
NOW, AND BECAUSE IT'S SUCH A BIG
COMMITMENT, WE DECIDE WE'RE
REMAINING ABSTINNENT UNTIL
MARRIAGE, AND IT'S THAT LEVEL OF
COMMITMENT THAT'S GOING TO TAKE
US ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
OH!
>> WELCOME, EVERYBODY!
>> WELCOME HOME, DAUGHTER!
>> MY FIRST STEPS ON TO THE NEW
COYOPA CAMP, IT'S GOOD.
I'M FEELING GOOD ABOUT IT SEE
HOW MUCH RICE THEY HAVE?
THEY'VE GOT A BUNCH OF RICE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHAT HAVE WE BEEN MISSING!
>> THERE'S FOOD HERE!
AND I WAS JUST LIKE, "YES!
WE GET TO EAT!
WE'RE DOWN TO HOW MANY-- HOW
MANY-- HOW MANY SCOOPS OF RICE.
>> WE HAVE ENOUGH FOR, LIKE,
THREE DAYS OF RICE.
>> I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN HAPPIER
BUT EVEN MORE IMPORTANTLY, I'M
ON THE SAME TRIBE WITH JACLYN.
>> I MISSED YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, WHERE'S THE WELL.
I SAW THE WELL.
>> I ALMOST CRIED SAID.
>> BEING HERE WITH JACLYN RIGHT
NOW IS A HUGE WEIGHT OFF MY
SHOULDERS.
SHE KNOWS EVERYTHING THAT'S
GOING ON IN MY LIFE, ESPECIALLY,
YOU KNOW, MY DAD RIGHT NOW IS--
IS DYING OF BRAIN CANCER.
JACLYN'S BEEN THERE FOR ME EVERY
STEP OF THE WAY.
AND I'M SO EXCITED THAT I CAN
ACTUALLY SHARE SOME OF THIS
EXPERIENCE WITH HER.
AND EVEN MORE EXCITED THAT IT
SEEMS LIKE, YOU KNOW, WE CAN
HELP EACH OTHER.
>> THIS HAPPENS, I NEEDED THIS.
I WAS THINKING TO MYSELF I DON'T
KNOW HOW MUCH MORE OF THIS I CAN
HANDLE.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT.
WHEN JON GOT A YELLOW BUFF, I
HAD NO IDEA WHAT IT MEANS FOR MY
INDIVIDUAL GAME.
IT'S UNHEARD OF TO HAVE SOMEONE
PLAYING WITH YOU THAT YOU TRUST
100%.
IT'S KIND OF CRAZY.
SO LET ME START FROM THE VERY
BEGINNING.
IT WAS ALL THE GUYS, AND THEN
BAYLOR WAS, LIKE, FLIPPING BACK
AND FORTH.
I DON'T TRUST BAIL OR OR JOSH
AND BAYLOR KNOWS THAT.
WE HAVE BEEN TOGETHER FOR THREE
YEARS AND WE DEFINITELY KNOW HOW
TO WORK TOGETHER AS A TEAM.
MY GOSH!
I CAN SLEEP WITH YOU?
>> I KNOW, RIGHT.
>> WE'VE JUST BEEN THROUGH SO
MUCH, AND IT'S GOOD THAT WE HAVE
THAT PAST SO WE KNOW HOW TO WORK
TOGETHER IN THIS KIND OF
SITUATION.
>> I MISSED YOU!
>> YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO HATE
US?
>> NO, I LOVE IT!
>> I LOVE IT!
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
SO CUTE.
JACLYN AND JON ARE IN LOVE.
UN, IT WAS KIND OF LIKE I WAS
WATCHING A HONEYMOON.
I'M TOTALLY JEALOUS.
I'M SITTING HERE SINGLE, 20,
HANGING OUT WITH MY MOM.
MY MOM AND I ARE BOTH SINGLE.
MAN, IT'S LIKE THAT TIME OF DAY
WHEN YOU'RE LIKE--
>> UH-HUH.
>> MY MOM HAS MADE HER SHARE OF
MISTAKES.
SHE'S BEEN MARRY THREED TIMES
AND DIVORCED THREE TIMES.
MY TIME WILL COME.
MY MOM'S NEXT TIME WILL COME.
>> SO YOU'RE A FISHERMAN?
>> WE'RE FIXING TO FIND OUT.
BRAND NEW TRIBE.
IT IS A LITTLE-- LITTLE BIT
WEIRD BEING ODD MAN OUT, WHICH I
DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S A MOMENT AND A
DAUGHTER.
IT'S A DADDY AND A DAUGHTER.
AND IT'S A GUY AND A GIRLFRIEND.
>> BRAD PITT.
>> YEAH, GIVE ME A BREAK!
I'M MUCH MORE HANDSOME THAN BRAD
PITT.
>> I'M KIND OF BETWEEN A ROCK
AND A HARD PLACE.
I MIGHT BE BY MYSELF BUT, YOU
KNOW, I GOT A LITTLE IDOL.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, IT'S IN MY
BOOT.
IF ALL ELSE FAILS, I GOT THE
BACKUP PLAN.
THAT'S ALWAYS AN ACE IN THE
HOLE.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE GOING TO BE
HUNGRY.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE WEIGHT.
YOUR BODY IS IT GOING TO SUFFER
BUT YOU WILL SURVIVE.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOUR
BROTHER THAT.
>> HE THOUGHT HE KNEW.
>> I FEEL PRETTY GOOD ABOUT THE
NEW TRIBE TO BE HONEST.
I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE THE MORE
ATHLETIC OF THE TWO TRIBES, SO
MAYBE MY TRIBE WON'T SUCK LIKE
THE LAST ONE.
I KNEW DREW COULDN'T ROUGH IT
FOR THAT LONG.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO TELL HIM.
I KNOW DREW AND HE WAS EITHER
VERY THIRSTY OR VERY HUNGRY OR
VERY SLEEP DEPRIVED.
IT'S DAY 11 AND I'M FINE.
I FEEL GOOD.
I THINK I HAVE PROVED I'M NOT IN
MY BROTHER'S SHADOW ANYMORE.
I OUTLASTED HIM IN THE GAME.
I EXPECTED MORE ON THE OF DREW
THAN THAT.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE I
CAN SAY I BEAT DREW.
>> I DON'T EVEN CARE BECAUSE--
>> I DON'T CARE, EITHER.
>> WE NEED HIM RIGHT NOW.
I CAN ONLY ASSUME THAT REED
JUMPED SHIP WITH JOSH, WES, AND
ALEC, SO, LIKE, I'M HOPING I CAN
JUST SAY TO ALEC, JUST ROLL WITH
US.
ALEC NEEDS TO REALIZE THAT HE
SHOULD BE WITH US.
>> HE'S SINGLE.
AND HE DOESN'T REALIZE THAT JOSH
WOULD BACKSTAB HIM AND WES IF IT
MEANT CHOOSING BETWEEN HIS BOO.
>> ALEC IS BY HIMSELF.
HE'S A SINGLE.
THE COUPLES ARE NOT GOING TO
BREAK THEIR BOND.
HE'S GOING TO BE OUT IF HE
STICKS WITH JOSH AND REED.
>> I GOTTA TALK TO THIS BOY ALEC
AND BE LIKE, "DUDE, REMOVE
YOURSELF FROM A THREESOME."
THREE AMEEGS SO NO MORE.
>> BECAUSE YOU HAVE REED WITH
THEM.
AS A FIREFIGHTER WE HAVE THIS
THING CALLED "SURROUND AND
DROWN."
SURROUND AND DRIEWN IS IF YOU'RE
FIGHTING A FIRE IN A BUILDING
AND IT GETS OUT OF CONTROL AND
YOU CAN'T EVEN GO INSIDE
ANYMORE, EVERYBODY STAY OUTSIDE
WITH THEIR HOSES, SURROUND IT
AND DROWN IT.
THAT'S WHAT WE NEED TO DO, WE
NEED TO DROWN HIM WITH THE WATER
OF THE SINGLES, YOU KNOW.
>> EITHER WAY, FOR PEOPLE LIKE
US, WHICH IS PEOPLE WITH
SINGLES, IF THE COUPLES EVEN
HAVE ONE MORE OVER US, THEY'RE
JUST GOING TO TAKE OUT SINGLES
ONE BY ONE.
>> ME, EITHER.
I'M BUMMED OUT, MAN.
>> HE DIDN'T HAVE THE HEART,
MAN.
>> HE DIDN'T.
>> YOU'VE GOT THE HEART.
I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO PLAY
ALEC'S EGO.
HE JUST LIKE HIS BROTHER.
HE'S JUST LIKE HIS BROTHER.
HE'S LIKE A LITTLE DREW.
BUT I'M STILL WORKING ON HIM.
IT'S SURROUND AND DROWN.
IT'S NOT OVER.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S MAKE RICE!
>> HOW MANY OF THESE DO YOU PUT
IN THERE?
>> HOWEVER MANY THERE ARE, PLUS
TWO.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED MORE, MOM.
>> DID BAYLOR GIVE YOU HER RICE
SCOOP, MISSY.
>> YEAH, THE LITTLE ONE?
>> YEAH.
>> ANOTHER THAT'S GOOD.
GIVE ME A STICK.
>> YOU WANT MORE?
>> ARE YOU KIDDING, YES!
>> OKAY.
>> THEY'RE PUTTING FIVE OR SIX
OF THOSE SCOOPS IN.
>> THAT DOES NOT LOOK LIKE
ENOUGH RICE, MOM.
>> OKAY, HE'LL TELLING ME THAT
I'M PUTTING TOO MUCH.
HE TOLD ME I DID WAY TOO MUCH.
SO I'M-- I MEAN, I'M JUST GOING
TO DO IT MY WAY FROM NOW ON.
>> THAT DOES NOT LOOK LIKE
ENOUGH IS ALL.
>> I AGREE.
I'LL DO ANOTHER BATCH.
>> GUYS, JUST MAKE A LITTLE
PORTION.
YOU HAVE ONE BAG OF RICE FOR 39
DAYS.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED, HE, LIKE,
TOLD YOU, HOW MANY CUPS?
>> HE WAS JUST LIKE MONITORING
ME.
I'M LIKE, "WHAT?"
THERE'S A TON OF RICE AT THIS
CAMP AND DALE WAS, LIKE OMONITOR
DUTY ABOUT HOW MUCH THEY HAD.
THAT'S NOT HOW WE DID IT OVER
THERE.
WE MADE SO MUCH MORE THAN THIS.
>> DALE'S BEEN TRYING TO GET ME
OFF SINCE THE BEGINNING, TOO.
>> MY DAUGHTER TOLD ME THAT DALE
HAS TRIED TO VOTE HER OUT PRETTY
MUCH THE ENTIRE TIME.
IT'S HARD WHEN YOU HEAR THAT
SOMEONE IS NOT BEING NICE TO JUR
KID.
I PROMISE YOU THIS THAT THAT'S
NOT A PROBLEM.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU, I MEAN,
BLOOD IS BLOOD.
SO IN THIS EXPERIENCE, THE ONLY
THING I WANT TO PREVENT MY KID
FROM IS THAT GUY PICKING ON HER.
>> ONE LESS MOUTH IN THREE DAYS.
OUR TRIBE HAS BEEN DOING REAL
GOOD ABOUT PRICE ROOIS.
WE'VE STILL GOT TWO-THIRD OF OUR
JUG LEFT, AND THEN MISSY COMES
IN AND STARTS DISHING OUT DOUBLE
HELPINGS.
I DIDN'T KNOW WE WERE EATING
NOW.
THAT MEANS NO DOUBLING UP THEN.
>> HAVE MORE.
I PROMISE YOU IT'S FINE.
>> I WAS BITING MY LIP HARD
ENOUGH TO DRAW BLOOD BECAUSE IT
TOOK EVERY BIT OF SELF-CONTROL
TO WALK OVER AND SLAP THE RICE
DISHES OUT OF THEIR HANDS AND
SAY, GIERKSES THIS IS MY CAMP,
THIS IS MY RICE, STAY AWAY FROM
IT."
>> I'M ALMOST WAITING FOR MISSY
AND MY DAD TO GET IN A BATTLE
OVER THE RICE.
I, LIKE, SEE IT-- I SEE IT
FORMING.
>> YOU WANT TO GO FOR A WALK SO
YOU CAN GET SOME FRESH AIR?
MISSY PLAYS THAT SWEET MOM ROLE,
BUT SHE CAN BE A BIT OF A DIVA,
AND MY DAD IS A SMALL-TOWN,
HARDWORKING FARM MAN, AND HE
DOESN'T DEAL WITH THAT KIND OF
STUFF.
>> WE CAN'T EAT TWICE SAY DAY.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU JUST HAVE
TO-- YOU DON'T WANT TO COME OFF,
YOU KNOW, LIKE AGGRESSIVE, AND
YOU'RE SAYING WHAT TO DO.
I'M REALLY HAPPY TO BE PLAYING
WITH MY DAD, BUT HE'S REALLY SET
IN HIS WAYS AND SAYS WHAT'S ON
HIS MIND SO THERE ARE CERTAIN
THINGS THAT HE DOES THAT I THINK
CAN BOTHER PEOPLE A LITTLE BIT.
>> I TAKE IT--
>> IT'S NOT WORTH CREATING THAT
DRAMA THAT--
>> I KNOW, I HAVE ALREADY PICKED
THAT UP FROM HER.
>> IN THE LONG RUN, GETTING IN A
FIGHT WITH SOMEONE OVER AN EXTRA
SCOOP OF RICE, IT COULD GET YOU
VOTED OUT NEXT TIME.
I'M GOG PLAY PEACEMAKER, I HAVE
TO.
OTHERWISE, HE WILL HAVE A BULL'S
EYE ON HIS BACK WHICH WILL PUT A
BULL'S EYE ON MY BACK.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> I HOPE IT STAYS THAT WAY BUT
I DOUBT IT WILL.
>> IT ALWAYS BURNS OFF.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE'RE LETHARGIC.
THAT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
>> WE HAVE, LIKE, 1.5 CUPS OF
RICE.
>> I DON'T WHAN WE'RE GOING TO
DO TO GET MORE FOOD.
FOOD IS GETTING DIRE.
WE'RE DOWN TO A HAND FULL OF
RICE, A HAND FULL OF BEANS, AND
IT TAKES ITS TOLL.
I WATCHED SEASON AFTER SEASON OF
THIS, AND I'M, LIKE, IT'S NOT
GOING TO BE GOOD.
>> ON OUR TRIBE, WE WERE EATING
ONCE A DAY.
WE COULD HAVE GONE 39 DAYS
EASILY THE WAY WE WERE GOING.
HERE WE HAVE THREE DAYS OF FOOD
LEFT?
AND THEN WHAT?
>> THOSE VULTURES ARE EATING
BETTER THAN US.
>> THEY'RE KILLING IT OUT THERE.
>> I'M SHOCKED, TO BE HONEST,
THAT PEOPLE WERE NOT SMARTER.
THERE WERE SOME VERY FOOLHARDY
PLAYERS ON THIS SIDE.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY FRUSTRATING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
DO.
>> DO YOU THINK WE COULD THROW A
BIG ROCK AT THAT FLOCK OF BIRDS
RIGHT THERE AND HIT ONE?
>> TO KILL A VULTURE, NO.
>> WHY.
>> ALL I SEE IS ROTISSERIE
CHICKENS RINNING AROUND OUT
THERE.
>> OH, MAN, THEY STINK.
THE JUICE ISN'T THE SQUEEZE.
I PROMISE.
>> WE HAVE TO HAVE FOOD.
WE LITERALLY HAVE NO FOOD LEFT.
>> WE MIGHT HAVE TO TRADE A
REWARD FOR MORE RICE, GUYS.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S GOING TO
BE THAT EASY.
>> YEAH.
>> WHATEVER WE'VE GOT TO DO,
LET'S GIVE JEFF SOMETHING.
I MEAN, WE NEED IT.
>> I FEEL LIKE THE LAST TIME WE
TRIED TO BART WER JEFF, IT KIND
OF MADE US ALL LOOK A LITTLE
FOOLISH BECAUSE THIS IS NOT
"SURVIVOR MARKET."
BUT IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAIRKZ
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO SETTLE FOR BECAUSE WE NEED
FOOD TO BE COMPETITIVE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO YOUR FIRST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE AS NEW
TRIBES?
>> YEAH.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
WILL TAKE IT PACK.
THANK YOU, BAYLOR.
>> SURE.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE IT TO DIG UP A
BACK CONTAINING TWO KEYS.
YOU WILL THEN CRAWL THROUGH THE
MUD.
YOU'LL USE ONE OF THE KEYS TO
OPEN A GATE.
YOU WILL THEN SHAKE A BASKET,
RELEASING SANDBAGS.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL YOUR
SANDBAGS, TWO TRIBE MEMBERS WILL
ATTEMPT TO LAND THOSE SANDBAGS
ON WOBBLY PLATFORMS.
FIRST TRIBE TO LAND 10 SANDBAGS
WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE
VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO!
FOR IMMUNITY!
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST STEP IS TO FIND THAT BAG
CONTAINING THE KEYS.
HUNAHPU THROWING A LOT OF SAND
QUICKLY.
COYOPA DIGGING A LITTLE MORE
CONSERVATIVELY.
TWO NEW TRIBES, ONE FULL OF
LOVED ONES, ONE FULL OF SINGLES.
WHICH TRIBE IS GOING TO WORK
TOGETHER BETTER?
THAT IS THE QUESTION.
>> HERE YOU GO!
HERE YOU GO!
HERE GU!
GLIRKS DISPL HUNAHPU HAS THEIR
BAG.
THEY'RE HEADED FOR THE MUD.
COYOPA STILL DIGGING.
GOTTA GO UNDER EVERYTHING!
EVERYBODY GETTING MUDDY!
ONCE AGAIN, COYOPA, AS A TRIBE,
IS BEHIND.
ONCE EVERYBODY'S AT THE GATE,
YOU CAN UNLOCK THE KEY.
HUNAHPU WITH A BIG LEAD.
COYOPA STILL LOOKING FOR THE
BAG.
>> NEVER GIVE UP.
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU IS THROUGH!
WES USING THE KEY TO OPEN THE
LOCK FOR HUNAHPU.
COYOPA HAS DUG UP THE ENTIRE PIT
AND STILL CAN'T FIND THE BA.
>> HERE IT IS!
>> I GOT A ROPE, ANYWAY.
>> Jeff: COYOPA HAS THE BAG!
THEY'RE HEADING FOR THE MUD!
COYOPA, YOU BETTER PICK IT UP!
HUNAHPU IS THROUGH.
EVERYBODY GET A HAND ON IT!
EVERYBODY!
START SHAKING.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR 20 SANDBAGS.
>> THERE THEY GO!
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU NOW THROWING
THEIR BAGS EVERYWHERE.
NOW THEY'VE GOT TO FIND THEM
ALL.
COYOPA'S THROUGH THE MUD.
HUNAHPU HAS ALL THEIR BAGS.
COYOPA, WAY BEHIND.
HUNAHPU TWO PEOPLE ARE TOSSING.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO LAND 10 BAGS
ON THE PLATFORM.
WES TOSSES FIRST FOR HUNAHPU.
JEREMY GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
HE'S SHORT.
COYOPA IS THROUGH THE GATE.
COYOPA NOW SHAKING THEIR BASKET.
WES WITH ANOTHER BAG.
THAT IS TWO.
MAKE IT THREE.
YOU NEED 10.
YOU'VE GOT TO SHAKE IT, COYOPA!
BACK AND FORTH.
IT WILL BEND.
BIG MOVE!
WORK TOGETHER.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
HUNAHPU WITH SIX.
YOU WOULD THINK THAT A TRIBE OF
LOVED ONES WOULD BE
COMMUNICATING BETTER THAN A
TRIBE OF STRANGERS.
SEVEN FOR HUNAHPU.
>> IT'S DONE!
IT'S DONE!
>> GET THE BAGS!
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU NOW WITH
EIGHT.
COYOPA HASN'T EVEN STARTED
TOSSING BAGS.
HUGE LEAD.
THAT IS NINE FOR HUNAHPU.
ONE MORE IS ALL IT TAKES.
JEREMY WINS IMMUNITY FOR
HUNAHPU!
THIS CHALLENGE IS OVER.
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
>> GOOD WORK!
>> GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: CLEARLY LOVED ONES
WORKING TOGETHER NOT SO
EFFECTIVELY.
HUNAHPU, IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER WHO'S ON THE TRIBE, THE
DOMINANCE CONTINUES.
( APPLAUSE )
IMMUNITY ONCE AGAIN FOR HUNAHPU.
NOBODY GOING THOAM IF ARE THIS
TRIBE.
COYOPA, THREE SETS OF LOVED ONES
STILL COULDN'T GET IT DONE.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY FROM THIS TRIBE WILL BE
VOTED OUT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> JEFF, WHEN YOU GET A S.E.C.,
WE'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU,
PLEASE?
>> Jeff: SURE.
I GOT TIME ANOTHER CONVERSATION.
THIS IS GOING TO BE GOOD.
>> SO WE JUST WANTED TO PRESENT
SOMETHING TO YOU.
WE'RE BASICALLY-- WE'RE OUT OF
FOOD.
AND OUR BEACH IS REALLY ARID, SO
WE'RE LOOKING TO MAKE A TRADE
FOR A BAG OF RICE TO SUSTAIN US.
>> I MEAN, WE WON TODAY, BUT
THAT WAS JUST ON ADRENALINE.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH FOOD IN OUR
SYSTEM.
>> Jeff: WES, WHERE ARE YOU AT
WITH THE RICE?
ARE YOU LITERALLY OUT?
>> WE GOT TWO, THREE SCOOPS.
>> TWO OF THIS.
>> I WOULDN'T SAY THAT.
>> NOT EVEN THAT.
>> IT'S A SCOOP TO WHERE WE GOT
A BITE FULL.
>> BIG GUYS ON THE OTHER TRIBE
RAN IT DOWN.
>> IT WAS REALLY FRUSTRATING.
ON COYOPA WE WERE LITERALLY
HAVING ONE MEAL A DAY.
THEY WERE EATING TWICE A DAY
EVERY DAY.
>> TWICE A DAIS DAYEXPWHR.
>> Jeff: AND HOW MUCH WERE YOU
GUYS EATING?
>> ONE TIME.
>> Jeff: WES, IT WOULD SOUND
LIKE COYOPA WHO IS RATIONING
WELL AND EEGHT ONE SMALL HELPING
A DAY, VERSUS HUNAHPU, WHO IS
EATING TWO BIG PORTIONS A DAY.
YOU CAN MAKE THE ARGUMENT THAT
MIGHT BE WHY THEY DID SO WELL IN
THE CHALLENGES.
>> YEAH.
YOU CAN MAKE THAT EASILY.
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY.
>> Jeff: SO THEN, AS A
CONSEQUENCE, REGARDLESS WHO IS
NOW ON THE TRIBE, THE TRIBE AS A
WHOLE HAS TO NOW PAY THAT
INVOICE.
THAT INVOICE WILL BE STEEP.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, I'VE GOT A
TRIBAL COUNCIL TO DEAL WITH.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAVE A LITTLE
BIT OF RICE.
ENJOY THAT TONIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW, AND WE'LL
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> THANK YOU.
>>
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF AND
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY YOUR NIGHT OFF.
>> JEFF SAID THAT HE WOULD COME
TO OUR CAMP TO DISCUSS SOME SORT
OF A TRADE.
WE NEED TO NEGOTIATE SOMETHING
IN ORDER TO GET MORE RICE.
BUT THAT'S REALLY GOING TO BE
HEAVY.
THAT'S GOING TO HIT HARD.
I'M NOT REALLY SURE WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN SO I'M SCARED.
SEEMS LIKE THESE THREE COUPLES
WOULD BE GUNNING TO GET ME.
THAT'S JUST A FREE VOTE.
THEY WOULDN'T LOSE NONE OF THEIR
LOVED ONES.
KEITH WOULD BE GONE.
EVERYTHING WOULD BE GOOD.
>> THAT WOULD BE A CRAZY ONE.
>> ANYBODY FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
BACK UP TO WHAT THEY WEIGHED
BEFORE WE STARTED THE GAME?
>> BUT THE THREE COUPLES, ONE
DON'T LIKE THE OTHER, AND THAT
COULD BE REAL GOOD FOR ME.
WE'LL SEE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> I'M SORRY, BUT I GOTTA JUST
DIP IN.
>> THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH MUD I
CAN STAND.
>> WE'VE GOT THREE COUPLES AND
KEITH.
SO IF YOU COULD GET ANOTHER
COUPLE ON YOUR SIDE, YOU CONTROL
OUR TRIBE.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
IT'S FOUR AGAINST THREE.
>> MY EAR!
>> THE WAY MISSY AND BAYLOR BOTH
HAVE BEEN AROUND CAMP ARE ONE OF
THE KEY THINGS DRIVING MY VOTE.
MISSY IS VERY PUSHY AROUND CAMP,
AND BAYLOR'S PROVEN IN THE PAST
SHE'LL TELL SOMEBODY TO VOTE ONE
WAY AND THEN SHE CHANGES HER
VOTE AT THE LAST MINUTE.
AND THAT MAKES YOU NERVOUS AS
HELL AT THIS STAGE OF THE GAME.
SO WE ABSOLUTELY HAVE TO WORK
WITH JON AND JACLYN BECAUSE
THEY'RE SWING VOTE.
NOW IT'S SCRAMBLE CITY.
AND THEN SHE SWAPPED HER VOTE
BACK TO NADIYA, SO ALL THE GIRLS
VOTED FOR ME.
>> OH.
>> SO SHE'S-- SO.
>> I DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S TOO RISKY, SCARY.
>> YEAH, SO--
>> BUT, MISSY IS?
>> SAME.
>> THAT SCARES ME, THOUGH.
>> AT THIS POINT IN TIME, MY DAD
AND I ARE DEFINITELY WORKING ON
JACLYN AND JON TRYING TO JUST
MAKE SURE THAT THEY'RE ON OUR
SIDE.
IF THE WHOLE POINT IS TO CHOOSE
A PAIR AND THAT'S THE NAME OF
THE GAME THEN I'M CHOOSING JON
AND JACLYN.
MISSY AND BAYLOR ARE OUT.
>> NEW TRIBE, NEW GAME.
WE START FROM SCRATCH NOW.
GOT YOUR BACK, MICHIGAN.
>> WE HAVE SO MANY COUPLES HERE,
IT REALLY IS ALL ABOUT FINDING
YOUR COUPLE THAT YOU MATCH UP
WITH.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS TO
BE ABLE TO READ A SITUATION AND
BE ABLE TO SAY IS THIS THE BEST
THING FOR ME NOW?
SO I'M LEAVING ROOM FOR MAKING
ADJUSTMENTS.
>> DALE SEEMS TO WANT TO BE WITH
YOU.
>> YEAH, DALE DEFINITELY DOES.
>> DALE DOESN'T TRUST BAYLOR.
>> BAYLOR OUT.
I DON'T KNOW WE HAVE TO FIGURE
OUT WHO WE'RE CLOSE WITH HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT'S
GOING ON.
WE HAVE TO TALK TO PEOPLE.
>> MAYBE GET TO KNOW PEOPLE
BETTER.
>> YES, THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE
NEED TO DO.
SO I DON'T KNOW IF YOU TWO HAVE
BEEN ON THE SAME SIDE THE WHOLE
TIME, BUT--
>> WELL, IN THE BEGINNING IT
SUCKED BECAUSE I IN TO GO WITH
THE GUYS.
SO IT LOOKED LIKE I WAS
COMPLETELY AGAINST THE GIRL
WHICH WAS SO ANNOYING BECAUSE I
LOVED YOU.
BUT I COULDN'T SAY ANYBODY EXWG
TO JACLYN YET BECAUSE I WAS WITH
THE GUYS.
SO I COULDN'T REALLY--
>> YEAH.
>> PART OF THE SWITCH, JACLYN
AND I NEVER REALLY WORKED
TOGETHER ONE ON ONE.
SO THIS IS-- THIS IS A NEW
BALLGAME WITH ME AND HER FOR
SURE.
SO, JACLYN, WHAT'S THE STORY
WITH DALE AROUND HERE?
WHAT'S THE VIBE?
WHAT'S THE RUB?
>> WELL, WE VOTED HIM OUT FIRST.
HE WAS MY FIRST VOTE.
ACTUALLY, HE WAS NEXT OUT.
>> I HATE TO SAY THIS, BUT THOSE
TWO COULD CERTAINLY BE A HUGE,
HUGE, HUGE THREAT TO THE END
BECAUSE THEY'RE SMART.
>> I THINK SO, TOO.
>> MY MOM AND I PUT SOME CARDS
ON THE TABLE.
HOPEFULLY THEY'LL CHOOSE US OVER
DALE AND KELLEY.
>> OKAY, SO, SHE'S OFF TO GO
LOOK FOR AN IDOL, I'LL BET YOU
100 BUCKS.
>> SHE IS SO DESPERATE.
>> WOW.
>> OKAY, LET'S SAY WORST CASE
SCENARIO, ONE OF THEM FIND IT.
ALL WE NEED IS THREE.
>> WHAT MAKES ME NERVOUS ABOUT
WORKING WITH MISSY AND BAYLOR
RIGHT NOW, JUST BECAUSE OF
BAYLOR'S PAST, THE BASIC IDEA IS
BAYLOR FLIPPED ON ME ONCE AND
SHE COULD DO IT AGAIN.
>> IT'S SO FRUSTRATING.
>> BUT DALE'S SNEAKY, AND I'M
SURE HIS DAUGHTER'S THE SAME
WAY.
>> I THINK MY DAD AND RIGOING TO
VOTE BAYLOR.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE WERE THINKING.
>> AND I'M NOT GOING TO TALK
ABOUT IT AGAIN TODAY.
>> MISSY AND BAYLOR WANT US, AND
KELLEY AND DALE WANT US, AND WE
BOTH KEEP TELLING THEM, "YEAH,
WE'RE IN."
>> I'VE GOT A GOOD FEELING.
>> IF WE'RE PLANNING ON TEAMING
UP WITH DALE ANDICLE, WE'RE
VOTING BAYLOR.
IF WE'RE TEAMING UP WITH BAYLOR
AND MISSY WE'RE SPLITTING VOTE
IN CASE THERE'S AN IMMUNITY IDOL
AND ONE OF THEM PLAYS IT.
>> TALK TOY ME.
ARE WE ALL GOOD?
>> WE'RE ALL GOOD.
THIS IS A BIG DECISION TONIGHT.
IT MAY DETERMINE WHAT COULD WE
WILL BE OR NOT BE PLAYING WITH
LATER.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO VOTE OUT
SOMEBODY'S LOVED ONE, AND
SOMEBODY'S NOT GOING TO BE
HAPPY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KEITH,
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THE NEW
TRIBE BECAUSE YOU LOOK AT THE
DIVISION, YOU HAVE THREE COUPLES
AND YOU.
DID YOU IMMEDIATELY FEEL THIS IS
NOT GOOD FOR ME?
>> INITIALLY, YES, BUT SOME OF
MY TEAMMATES COME WITH ME, TOO,
SO IT SEEMED LIKE IT WAS GOOD
AND BAD, TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
YOU KNOW WHERE I'M GETTING THAT?
>> Jeff: I'M LISTENING.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, JEFF.
I HOPE IT'S NOT 6-1.
IF IT IS I'VE BEEN REALLY HAD.
>> Jeff: WELL, JACLYN, YEAH,
YOU TONIGHT YOU COULD MAKE IT A
VERY EASY VOTE AND TAKE OUT
KEITH BUT THAT'S ONLY ONE
TRIBAL.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TWO COUPLES ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO GANG UP ON ONE AT
SOME POINT.
>> THAT MAKES IT HARDER BECAUSE
ONE PERSON OUT OF A COUPLE GOES
HOME AND YOU HAVE TO MAINTAIN
RELATIONSHIPS STILL.
SO IT MAKES IT EVEN HARD THEY'RE
THEY'RE ON THE SAME TRIBE AS US.
>> Jeff: JON, NOW HERE YOU
FIND YOURSELF WITH SEVEN PEOPLE
LEFT, AN ODD NUMBER AND SHE THE
TIME TO MAKE A MOVE TYPICALLY IS
WITH ODD NUMBERS.
DID YOU FEEL COUPLES SCOPING
EACH OTHER OUT TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT IS THE MOVE?
>> ABSOLUTE.
YOU CAN CAN'T GET SOMEBODY TO
ALIGN WITH YOU OF IF YOU DON'T
HAVE A CONVERSATION WITH THEM.
I TALKED TO JACK LIP, WHO IS MY
DPOIFL, SO THAT'S VERY HELPFUL.
I CAN TRUST SOMEONE 100%.
>> Jeff: DALE DYOU AND KELLEY
TALK TO BOTH OTHER COUPLES?
>> BAYLOR AND I SPEAK VERY
LITTLE BECAUSE WE'VE HAD AN
ONGOING ROCKY RELATIONSHIP, I
GUESS.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, WHEN THERE
ARE THREE COUPLES AND ONE OF
THEM, DALE AND KELLEY, HAS
FRICTION WITH YOU, THIS COULD
PUT YOU A LITTLE BIT ON THE OUT.
>> I MEAN, I THINK SINCE OF
BEGINNING OF OUR ORIGINAL TRIBE,
ME AND DALE JUST HAVEN'T REALLY
HAD A CHANCE TO GET TO KNOW EACH
OTHER.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I DISLIKE
DALE.
THINS GOT CRAZY.
>> BUT AT THE SAME TIME, BAYLOR
PUT ALL GIRLS OUT THERE TO VOTE
FOR ME AND THEN SHE SWAPPED HER
VOTE BACK TO ALIGN WITH THE
GUYS.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, THIS COULD BE
GREAT NEWS FOR AND YOU JON
BECAUSE IF DALE ANDICLE RENOT
GETTING ON WITH MISSY AND
BAYLOR, THAT MAKES YOU TWO THE
COUPLE TO GO TO.
>> IT DOES.
IT DEFINITELY PUTS US IN THAT,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF A GOOD
POSITION WHERE WE HAVE TO BE
REALLY STRATEGIC ON WHO WE
DECIDE TO GO WITH AND WHO WE
VOTE OUT.
>> TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
THEY'RE THE HOTTEST COUPLE IN
CAMP RIGHT NOW.
>> THEY'RE THE HOTTEST COUPLE,
PERIOD.
>> Jeff: KELLEY, YOU SEE THAT,
TOO, THAT JON AND JACLYN, THEY
ARE THE COUPLE IN THE MIDDLE AND
THEY'RE GOING TO DECIDE TONIGHT
WHO TO GO WITH?
>> I THINK THAT'S ONE WAY TO PUT
IT.
NOW, OBVIOUSLY WITH MY DAD AND
BAYLOR NOT BEING ON THE BEST
TERMS I WASN'T THE FIRST TO GO
TO BAYLOR AND SAY, LET'S LINK UP
AND GET AN ALLIANCE GOING."
>> Jeff: WHAT IS THAT LIKE TO
COME INTO A TRIBE AND FIND OUT
YOUR DAD HAS AN ISSUE WITH
BAYLOR THAT IS STARTING THE GAME
WAY BURDEN?
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTE.
IT'S LIKE A 50-POUND BACKPACK ON
THERE DRAGGING US DOWN.
>> Jeff: ON THE OTHER SIDE,
MISSY, MAYBE IT'S TO JON'S AND
JACLYN'S ADVANTAGE TO GET RID OF
YOU OR BAYLOR.
>> WELL, I MEAN ALL THAT'S
SPINNING THROUGH MY HEAD RIGHT
NOW IS THAT MOMMA BEAR.
I CAN'T EVEN GET PAST THE FACT
THAT DALE HAS BASICALLY BEEN
GUNNING FOR MY DAUGHTER THE
WHOLE TIME WITHOUT ME THERE.
I'M KIND OF STUCK ON THAT.
>> WASN'T SHE GUNNING FOR HIM
FIRST?
>> YEAH, I DIDN'T GO AFTER
BAYLOR FIRST.
SHE CAME AFTER ME FIRST.
>> YOU KNOW, AT THE END OF THE
DAY, I DID TELL THE GIRLS MAYBE
THAT'S THE PERSON WE SHOULD VOTE
OUT.
IT'S THE FIRST TRIBAL.
NO ONE KNOWS WHAT TO DO.
>> Jeff: MISSY, WHAT MAKES YOU
THINK HE WAS GOING AFTER BAYLOR.
>> IT'S WHAT SHE TOLD ME, HE PUT
MY NAME DOWN.
IT DOES PUT A HUGE DAMPER
BETWEEN ME AND KELLEY.
NOT ONLY IS KELLEY HAVING A
50-POUND BACKPACK ON HER FOR MY
KID BUT NOW SHE HAS 50 MORE FROM
ME BECAUSE I'M GOING TO PROTECT
MY KID.
THAT'S JUST A NO-BRAINER.
>> Jeff: KEITH, YOU'RE A DAD.
YOU HAVE TWO PARENTS WHO ARE
TRYING TO PROTECT THEIR KIDS BUT
IN DOING SO MAY BE SCREWING UP
THEIR GAME.
>> RIGHT.
AND I GUESS IT'S GOOD FOR ME.
BUT I'M WITH MISSY AND WITH
DALE.
I MEAN, IT'S BLOOD.
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO BE
DISAPPOINTED TODAY.
AND I JUST HOPE WE CAN GET OVER
THAT HUMP AS A TRIBE.
>> Jeff: IT REALLY DOES PUT
JACLYN AND JON'S IN THE MIDDLE
BECAUSE YOUR VOTE IS NOT ENOUGH.
>> ROGER.
>> AND, JEFF, THE DRAWBACK TO
THIS ENTIRE SCENARIO, BLOOD
VERSUS WATER, YOU'RE VOTING
SOMEONE'S LOVED ONE OUT.
AND IT SUCKS.
THIS IS TAKING IT TO THE NEXT
LEVEL BECAUSE IF IT HAPPENS
TONIGHT YOU GO BACK TO CAMP WITH
THEM.
THERE'S NO WAY TO VOTE SOMEBODY
OUT AND FEEL GOOD IF IT BECAUSE
YOU'RE VOTING SOMEBODY ELSE'S
LOVED ONE OUT OF THE GAME.
>> Jeff: OKAY, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
BAYLOR, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, BAYLOR.
KELLEY.
BAYLOR.
TWO VOTES KELLEY, TWO VOTES
DALE.
ONE VOTE DALE.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES DALE, TWO VOTES
KELLEY, TWO VOTES BAYLOR.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF "BLOOD
VS. WATER," KELLEY.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
KELLEY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: WELL, AFTER TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL, ONE QUESTION LOOMS--
AFTER VOTING OUT A LOVED ONE,
CAN YOU GO BACK TO CAMP AND WORK
TOGETHER AS A TRIBE?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
DALE GAMBLES WITH HIS FAKE IDOL.
>> I'M NOT DEAD UNTIL I SEE MY
NAME WRITTEN FOUR TIMES.
>> Jeff: WHILE HUNAHPU FIND
NOTHING COMES WITHOUT A PRICE.
>> Jeff: THERE HAS NEVER BEEN
A TRIBE THAT HAS NEEDED AS MUCH
HELP AS YOU GUYS HAVE, AND IT'S
GOING TO BE A STIFF PENALTY.
>> I ALMOST WISH I DIDN'T PLAY
WITH MY DAD.
I I THINK IT WAS MORE OF A
HINDRANCE THAN A HELP FOR ME.
I WOULD TRADE ANYTHING TO BE
BACK ON MY OLD TRIBE AND STILL
IN THE GAME.
AND FOR HIM, TO NOT PLAY WITH
HIM AT ALL, ESPECIALLY AMING
INTO COYOPA, PEOPLE ARE NOT A
HUGE FAN OF HIM IN THE COYOPA
TRIBE.
SO, YOU KNOW, IT JUST DID NOT GO
IN MY FAVOR BECAUSE OF THAT.