>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": HUNAHPU WAS
STARVING.
>> WE'RE DOWN TO JUST, LIKE, A
HAND FULL OF RICE.
>> Jeff: AND DECIDED TO TRADE
NEARLY EVERYTHING FOR A BAG OF
RICE.
I WANT YOUR TARP, PILLOWES,
BLANKETS, YOU ARE STARTING OVER.
AND NO ONE FELT IT MORE THAN
JULIE.
>> I CAN'T DO THIS ALL NIGHT.
I CAN'T.
LAST NIGHT WAS THE HARDEST NIGHT
OF MY LIFE.
>> Reporter:
>> Jeff: BUT DESPITE LOSING
EVERYTHING-- DO THEY HAVE IT
RIGHT?
HUNAHPU WON THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
THEY DO.
HUNAHPU WINS ONCE AGAIN.
>> WE CAN'T CATCH A BREAK.
IT IS FRUSTRATING.
>> Jeff: BACK AT CAMP, DALE
WAS IN TROUBLE AND HOPED HIS
FAKE IMMUNITY IDOL COULD KEEP
HIM IN THE GAME.
>> IF I'M NOT VOTED OUT TONIGHT,
I'LL GIVE YOU MY IDOL.
>> DUDE.
>> RIGHT NOW I'M BARTERING THAT
IDOL FOR VOTES.
>> Jeff: WORRIED THAT THE IDOL
WAS REAL, THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE
DECIDED TO SPLIT THE VOTE
BETWEEN DALE AND THEIR ALLY,
KEITH.
>> THREE VOTES DALE TWO KEITH.
>> I'M SAD ABOUT THAT, BUT
BETTER KEITH THAN ME.
>> Jeff: AND AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL-- KEITH.
KEITH WAS SHOCKED TO GET VOTES.
BUT IN THE END, IT WAS DALE WHO
WAS SENT HOME.
DALE, YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
DALE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
LEAVING KEITH CONFUSED AND IN
THE DARK.
12 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> LAST NIGHT, WE VOTED DALE
OUT, BUT THERE HAD BEEN SO MUCH
PARANOIA AND TALK OF HIM HAVING
AN IDOL, WE DECIDED BAYLOR AND I
WOULD WRITE KEITH, BUT I KNEW IT
WASN'T GOING TO SIT PRETTY.
NO ONE LIKES TO HAVE THEIR NAME
WRITTEN DOWN.
KEITH, I WANT TO TALK ABOUT LAST
NIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE I KEPT SOMETHING
FROM YOU, AND IF YOU WERE IN THE
SAME POSITION AS ME AND YOU HAD
WES OVER HERE AND I WAS BY
MYSELF, AND YOU THOUGHT THERE
WAS EVEN A SHOT THAT DALE WAS
GOING TO SHOW UP WITH AN IDOL, I
WAS TRYING TO FLUSH IT.
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO
SEND HER HOME.
AND I I DIDN'T WANT TO GO HOME
BUT I WASN'T SURE THE WHO HECK
HE WAS GOING TO PUT DOWN.
>> YOU COULD HAVE LET ME KNOW.
WHEN I SAW MY NAME COME UP TWICE
AT TRIBAL I SAID, "WHAT IN THE
WORLD?"
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
MY NAME WASN'T IN THE PLAN.
DIMISS THE MEMO?
WHAT IF DALE WOULD HAVE VOTE FOR
ME.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN 3-3.
>> WE WOULD HAVE DONE A REVOTE
AND WE ALL WOULD HAVE VOTED FOR
DALE.
>> DALE WAS ALWAYS WHO WE WANTED
TO GO HOME.
>> MORE LYING.
I MEAN, WE DON'T HAVE TO LIE.
>> I KNOW.
>> EVERY OTHER BREATH WE DON'T
HAVE TO LIE.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, YOU WERE A
BIG PART OF THIS.
>> I THINK WE COULD MAKE THIS
HAPPEN BUT WHEN STUFF LIKE THAT
HAPPENS, IT MAKES YOU FEEL LIKE
I AIN'T TOO SURE.
IT WAS MISSY AND BAYLOR THAT
VOTED FOR ME AND THEY GIVE ME
SOME LAME EXCUSE.
WELL, I NEED SOMEBODY THAT STAYS
LOYAL.
I'M DONE WITH YOU ALL.
I'LL LEAVE YOU HANGING HIGH AND
DRY.
>> WE GOT TREE MAIL!
>> OH, MY GOD.
"GATHER YOUR VALUABLE BELONGS
AND FOLLOW THE MAP TO THE
HEADLAND TRAIL.
CONTINUE TO THE TOP OF THE HILL
WHERE YOU WILL RECEIVE FURTHER
INSTRUCTIONS.
UPON.
>> MERGE.
>> WE MADE IT GUYS.
>> LET'S PACK UP.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
WE.
>> WE GOT OUR TREE MAIL THAT
BASICALLY SAID WE WERE MERGED.
IT WAS A MIXED EMOTION FEELING
AT THAT POINT BECAUSE WE NEEDED
TO GET RID OF JEREMY, AND WE
DIDN'T DO IT WHEN WE HAD THE
CHANCE BECAUSE WE HAVE NOT GONE
TO TRIBAL WITH THIS FULL TRIBE.
NOW IT MAKES IT A LITTLE MORE
PRECARIOUS TO GET JEREMY OUT,
BUT WE CAN TO THIS.
>> ALEX AND WES ARE TOTALLY ON
BOARD WITH US, AND KEITH WOULD
EASILY COME OVER.
THAT'S FIVE.
>> IN THIS GAME I SAY YOU HAVE
UPS AND DOWNS AND UPS AND DOWNS.
I WAS DOWN.
WE'RE MERGING, BOYSES.
>> TIME TO RUN THE GAME.
>> YEAH.
>> AND AT HUNAHPU, REED AND
JOSH WERE IN CHARGE.
AND THEY RAN IT.
AND I TOOK A BACKSEAT, AND
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS HAVE YOUR
FUN.
>> LET'S DO THIS.
BUT IT'S MERGE TIME.
NOW IT'S TIME TO VOTE, AND I
WANT TO CRUSH THEM.
Captioning sponsored by
Survivor Productions, CBS
GATHER YOUR VALUABLE
BELONGINGS AND FOLLOW THIS MAP
TO THE HEADLAND TRAIL."
>> OH, MY GOD!
WE'RE MERGING.
>> I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE.
>> MERGE!
>> WE GOT TREE MAIL AND IT SAID,
"PACK YOUR THINGS.
WE ARE MERGING."
>> NOBODY WANTS TO DATE SOMEBODY
THAT DOESN'T MAKE IT TO THE
MERGE.
WE CAN STILL DATE EACH OTHER
BECAUSE WE STILL WANT TO--
>> I'M EXCITED.
IT'S A MILESTONE FOR ME AND JON
TO MAKE THE MERGE TOGETHER.
WE NEVER THOUGHT THIS WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED.
>> GOOD-BYE, COYOPA.
>> AND NOW HERE WE ARE BOTH
GOING INTO IT DAY 16 OF THE
MERGE, ONCE WE GET TO THE
OTHER SIDE WE'LL FEEL IT OUT
BECAUSE WE ARE DEFINITELY
KEEPING OUR OPTIONS OPEN.
>> COMING INTO THE MERGE, IT'S A
WHOLE NEW CHAPTER.
YOU'RE ALL COMING BACK TOGETHER.
YOU'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
STILL STANDS AND WHAT DISSPATED
AND THERE'S THIS BLOOD VERSUS
WATER ELEMENT.
YOU HAVE A NATURAL ALLIANCE
BUILT IN THAT IS SO APPARENT,
AND YOU HAVE PEOPLE WHO DON'T
HAVE THEIR LOVED ONES IN THE
GAME ANYMORE SO IT WILL BE TWO
INTERESTING TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
( CHEERS )
>> FOOD!
>> I LOVE FOOD!
>> GUYS, THIS IS TOTALLY WORTH
ALL THE SUFFERING.
>> I'M DYING RIGHT NOW!
> HAVING ABSOLUTELY NOTHING FOR
16 DAYS AND THEN SEEING THIS
GIANT FEAST WAITING, AND IT'S
GOT CHEESE AND TRAIL MIX AND
BOOZE AND LOBSTER AND SHRIMP AND
IT'S AWESOME!
SWEET!
>> CONGRATULATIONS ON MAKING IT
TO THE MERGE, GUYS.
>> SUCH A MILESTONE, MAKING THE
MERGE.
LITERALLY AND MENTALLY.
>> ON OUR PREVIOUS TRIBE, WE
JUST HAD ONE COUPLE AND THAT WAS
REED AND JOSH.
THAT WAS A LITTLE ANNOYING, YOU
KNOW, KIND OF SEEING THEM HAVING
THEIR LOVERS' VACAY.
NOW WE ARE MERGED AND HAVE
MULTIPLE LOVED ONE TOGETHER AND
IT'S REALLY TOUGH ON ME BECAUSE
I MISS MY BOYFRIEND JOHN.
I KIND OF WANT TO SEPARATE
MYSELF FROM THE GROUP AND GO CRY
A LITTLE BIT.
>> "CONGRATULATIONS, YOU ARE
MERGED.
ENJOY YOUR CELEBRATION THEN HEAD
YOUR NEW HOME, THE FORMER COYOPA
CAMP.
THE GAME CONTINUES."
>> YAY!
>> YAY.
>> WE'RE GOING GREEN, GUYS.
>> THAT FEAST WAS THE NUMBER ONE
HIGHLIGHT OF THIS GAME SO FAR.
EVERYTHING WAS GREAT.
WE HAD TO TAKE ALL THE FOOD LEFT
HOME TOW WE COULD HAVE A FEAST
TOMORROW, TOO.
>> I'M TAKING ALL OF THIS.
>> YEAH, JULIE, GOOD CALL.
>> I'M EXCITED TO PLAY WITH WES.
IT'S BEEN 16 DAYS, AND YEAH IT
WAS GOOD TO SEE HIM.
>> WHEN SHE WAS BORN, I WAS,
LIKE, DIVORCED.
>> I COULD CARE LESS ABOUT MISSY
AND BAYLOR.
>> I NEED TWO MORE GUYS OVER
HERE ON THIS.
>> THE GAME ALL OF A SUDDEN
SLIKE, SPEEDING.
BECAUSE YOU'RE DOING SO MUCH,
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH EXHAUSTION.
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH JUST MENTAL
MIND CRAZINESS.
AND THEN TO ADD ON TO ALL THAT,
THE ELEMENTS OUT HERE.
IT'S NOT EASY.
>> ARE YOU GOOD?
>> BUT NOW WE'RE MERGED.
AND IT'S A LITTLE DAUNTING WITH
SO MANY PEOPLE, AND IT'S A
LITTLE SCARY, AND IT'S A LITTLE
UNCOMFORTABLE BECAUSE THIS IS
WHERE YOU MAKE OR BREAK IF
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE THE NUMBERS
FOR THE REST OF THIS GAME.
>> WELCOME HOME, GUYS.
>> WE'RE EACH OTHER'S LOVED
ONES.
>> THE MERGE IS A MILESTONE, BUT
I THINK EVEN MORE THAN THAT,
THIS IS WHERE THE GAME STARTS.
LIKE, THE FIRST HALF OF THE GAME
IS THOSE ARE PRELIMBS, YOU KNOW.
THIS IS THE TOTAL DIFFERENT
LEVEL OF PLAY.
LIKE, WE HAVE TO ALL STEP OUR
GAMES OUT.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> EVERYTHING GOOD?
>> YEAH, THESE DAYS ARE TOUGH,
TO SEE EVERYBODY WITH THEIR
PERSON.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT.
>> IT MAKES IT SO--
>> IT HURTS.
>> IT AIN'T RIGHT.
IT AIN'T RIGHT AT ALL.
>> JUST KNOW WHATEVER YOU'RE
FEELING, I'VE GOT THE SAME
THING.
>> YEAH.
THE ONLY WAY I'M GOING TO
CONTINUE ON IN THIS CASE GAME IS
IF I CAN KEEP NUMBERS SO I HAVE
MYSELF, NAT, ALWAYS JULIE.
JULIE'S JUST OUR NUMBER.
NOW I NEED TO GET TWO COUPLES,
JON-JACLYN, AND MISSY AND
BAYLOR.
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT OVER HERE?
>> OBVIOUSLY, MISSY AND US ARE
STILL COOL.
>> GOOD.
>> BUT WES IS DOWN WITH?
>> JOSH.
>> AND JOSH IS RUNNING
EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH.
>> JOSH IS ON HIS GAME RIGHT
NOW.
AS SOON AS I GOT HERE, THERE
WERE A FEW PEOPLE I WANTED TO
TALK TO, BUT JON WAS NUMBER ONE
ON THE LIST.
>> SO WE GOT THE FOUR THAT WERE
HERE RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> AT LEAST.
AND THEN AT LEAST YOU AND
NATALIE AND JULIE.
>> YEAH.
>> SO WE HAVE SEVEN.
SO SO WE VOTE JOSH.
>> THE FIRST VIBE I GOT FROM JON
WAS A GOOD JOB.
HE HAS JACLYN.
I SAID WE'RE GOOD.
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER.
WE'RE MOVINGED FOR.
>> OKAY, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> SO WE'RE GOOD.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
>> WE HAVE NATE, JULIE, YOU,
BAYLOR, AND WE'VE STILL GOT JON
AND JACLYN.
SO WE'VE GOT SEVEN.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
I KNOW WE'RE GOOD.
>> WE'VE BEEN THAT WAY SINCE THE
BEGINNING.
I'M GLAD TO HAVE YOU BACK!
>> MISSY'S BEEN WITH ME SINCE
DAY ONE.
I KNOW I HAVE MISSY AND MISSY
WILL BRING BAYLOR.
WE HAVE SEVEN.
THAT'S ALL WE NEED.
>> WE NEED TO COME UP WITH
ANOTHER TRIBE NAME.
>> HUOPA.
>> A COMBINATION OF THE TRIBES.
>> ALLIANCES ARE CRAZY RIGHT
NOW, AND THERE'S A LOT OF MAYHEM
AND A LOVE TALKING GOING ON.
I THINK JEREMY'S BEEN TALKING TO
EVERYONE.
HE'S JUST TRYING TO GATHER HIS
TROOPS AROUND BECAUSE HE KNOWS
IT COULD BE THE COUPLES.
>> HASHTAG HUOYOPA.
>> HUOYOPA.
>> THE GOAL IS TO MAKE SURE
JEREMY DOESN'T GET THE NUMBERS
BEFORE WE GET THE NUMBERS.
BECAUSE BECAUSE IF NOT, I'M
SCREWED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
>> YES, IT WAS.
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> THANK YOU, JOSH.
FIRST PERSON TO TELL ME THAT.
AND I'VE BEEN TALKING TO HIM ALL
MORNING.
>> IT'S WESLEY'S BIRTHDAY TODAY.
AS A MATTER OF FACT I WOKE UP
THIS MORNING AND FORGOT ALL
ABOUT IT AND JOSH WISHED HIM
HAPPY BIRTHDAY BEFORE I DID.
HERE YOU GO, HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
ROASTED YOU A CRAB.
>> YOU GOT ONE FOR REAL.
>> DON'T EVER SAY YOUR DAD
DIDN'T PROVIDE FOR YOU.
>> ENJOY YOUR CRAB IN NICARAGUA.
I DID FORGET FOR A MINUTE, BUT
NO BIG DEAL, I DID REMEMBER AND
WISHED HIM A HAPPY EXPWGD
EVERYTHING IS GOOD, HAPPY
BIRTHDAY RIGHT HERE ON THE
BEACH.
>> JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
PEOPLE ARE NOT SEEING WHAT
JEREMY IS DOING.
>> I GIVE HIM PROPS BECAUSE HE'S
DOING A GREAT JOB.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> THERE ARE FOUR PEOPLE WHO ARE
SINGLES, AND EIGHT PEOPLE WHO
ARE COUPLES.
SO I'M THINKING, WHY DON'T WE
STICK TOGETHER AS COUPLES AND BE
ABLE TO GET DOWN TO NUMBERS WITH
THE PEOPLE WE LOVE.
>> I'M GONNA GUILTY ON BAYLOR
TODAY.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE REALLY DOES OWE ME ONE,
LIKE, AND I'M GONNA CALL HER OUT
ON THE FACT THAT WE'VE HAD AN
ALLIANCE FROM THE BEGINNING.
>> YEAH.
>> RIGHT NOW, MY TIGHTEST
ALLIANCE IS ME AND REED, ALEC,
WES, AND KEITH.
BUT THAT'S STILL FIVE.
WE NEED AT LEAST SEVEN.
SO I THINK I CAN STILL GET
BAYLOR TO VOTE WITH ME BECAUSE I
DID SAVE HER ONCE.
AND MISSY IS GOING TO TRANSFER
WITH BAYLOR TO ME.
>> I'M EXCITED TO SEE YOU.
>> DUDE, ME, TOO.
>> ARE WE STILL GOOD?
>> AS FAR AS I KNOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN--
>> OKAY.
OH, MY GOD, YOUR HAIR.
>> I KNOW.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> AND WITH YOU WE HAVE THE
NUMBERS.
>> OH, DANG.
IT'S DIFFICULT BECAUSE MY MOM
HAS A BUNCH OF ALLIANCES.
I ONLY HAVE ONE STRONG ONE WITH
JOSH.
AND AND SHE'S WITH JON, JACLYN,
JEREMY, NATALIE.
AND BEING ALIGNED WITH JOSH
STILL IS REALLY DIFFICULT FOR ME
RIGHT NOW.
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO HAVE FOUR
COUPLES.
YOU DON'T WANT TO SIDE WITH THE
SINGLE PLAYERS BECAUSE THEN
YOU'RE GOING TO BE TARGETED.
>> STARTING OUT THE GAME, ME AND
JOSH IMMEDIATELY ALIGNED.
AND HE PRETTY MUCH PROTECTED ME.
THAT'S WHAT'S HARDEST FOR ME IS
BEING LIKE, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR HELPING ME.
NOW I HAVE TO VOTE YOU OUT.
I NEED TO DIGEST AND COME BACK
TO LIFE AND I'M GOING TO GET
BACK IN WITH LIFE AND YOU.
>> NO, NO, TOTALLY, JUST WANT
YOU TO KNOW I STILL HAVE YOUR
BACK.
I CHATTED WITH BARELY AND I'M
LIKE I SAVED YOUR LIFE NOW WE
COME OVER HERE AND YOU'RE GOING
TO IGNORE THAT COMPLETELY?
I I HONESTLY, WAS A LITTLE HURT.
>> IT FEELS SKETCHY?
>> YES, VERY SKETCHY.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE SHE'S HERE
WITH MISSY.
>> I KNOW, BUT IT'S OUR ONLY
CASE RIGHT NOW.
>> EXACTLY.
>> JOSH CAME UP TO ME ALREADY
AND HE HE WAS LIKE.
ARE WE GOOD?
AND I SAID AS FAR AS I KNOW.
HE SAID ME AND YOU.
THAT'S GOING TO REALLY MAKE ME
SAD.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE A
CONVERSATION JOSH, MOM.
HE SAID I HAVE YOUR BACK.
ME AND REED HAVE YOUR BACK.
SHOOT.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BE A
LITTLE BIT PHONY.
>> I KNOW I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
BE PHONY BUT I WANT TO MAKE SURE
HE WILL RESPECT ME IN THE END
FOR VOTING HIM OUT.
>> HE WILL RESPECT YOU AS A
PLAYER WHEN YOU BLINDSIDE HIM.
JUST SAY I WAS WITH MY MOM.
>> YOU AND HIM ARE EQUAL BUT
YOU'RE MY MOM AND I'M GOING TO
GO WITH YOU,OB.
>> BAYLOR IS 20, AND SOMETIMES
SHE ACTS LIKE SHE'S 30, AND
SOMETIMES SHE ACTS LIKE SHE'S
10.
SHE HAS THIS NEED TO PLEASE.
BUT SHE'S GOING TO HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO HANDLE HER
HEART BECAUSE SHE DOES HAVE A
SWEETHEART, WHEN IT COMES DOWN
TO VOTING REED OR JOSH OUT.
OKAY, YOU HAVE TO DO WHAT I SAID
BECAUSE I'VE ALREADY TALKED TO
JEREMY AND HE AND I ARE STILL
LIKE THAT, LIKE WE WERE AT THE
BEGINNING.
>> OKAY.
>> BAYLOR-- BAYLOR, WE HAVE THE
BERS AND JOSH KNOW KNOWS AND AND
JOSH IS FREAKING OUT.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S A GAME.
SUCK IT UP.
JUST SMILE, AND BE LIKE, "OH,
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I'LL TALK TO MY MOM."
OKAY.
BUT JUST SMILE TO EVERYBODY
RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW SHE RESPECTS ME, BUT
THE DIFFERENCE TO ME IS SHE'S
COMING TO ME AND ASKING ME
QUESTIONS AND IT FEELS PRETTY
GOOD.
IT'S LIKE, OKAY, YEAH, I'VE MADE
SOME BAD DECISIONS IN MY LIFE
AND SHE HAD TO STAND BY AND
WATCH THEM AND I FEEL PRETTY
CRAPPY ABOUT THAT.
NO MOM IS PROUD TO BE DIVORCED
ONE, TWO, OR THREE TIMES AND
ESPECIALLY HAVING TO HAVE YOUR
KID WATCH YOU GO THROUGH IT.
BUT I GET TO REDEEM MYSELF AND
SHE'S WATCHING IT.
SHE'S BACK TO BEING MY KID AND
SHE'S LISTENING TO ME.
I'M LIKE TRUST ME ON THIS.
FOLLOW MY LEAD.
GET IN THE BACK SEAT AND LET ME
DRIVE.
WE'RE GOING TO HEAD DOWN THIS
PATH AND WE'LL BE FINE BUT YOU
HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME.
>> I FEEL LIKE THE TIME THAT
BAIL OFFICE AWAY FROM ME, THAT
SHE REALLY GOT UNDER HER MOM'S
INFLUENCE IN DIVERTING HER AWAY
FROM MYSELF AND REED SO NOW I
HAVE NO OTHER OPTION.
BESIDES JON AND JACLYN, WE HAVE
TO MAKE A PLAY FOR THESE PEOPLE
OR WE WILL BE OUT OF THE
NUMBERS.
>> I THINK THAT LOOKS REALLY
GOOD.
THAT IS REALLY COOL.
I LIKE THE COLORS.
>> HEY, YOU GUYS CAN I JUST SAY
SOMETHING TO YOU.
>> YES.
>> REED AND I REALLY WOULD LOVE
TO WORK WITH YOU GUYS.
WE FEEL LIKE GETTING IN BED WITH
JEREMY, I THINK HE IS GONNA BE
THE STRONGEST COMPETITOR.
HE'S THE ONE WORKING WITH THE
MOST.
HE'S THE ONE TALKING TO.
AND--
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN AND SO
JUST IN A PERSPECTIVE THING, WHO
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE GOING TO
GIVE A MILLION DOLLARS TO, TWO
BROADWAY GUYS WHO ARE VERY
SUCCESSFUL OR A FIREMAN WHO HAS
TWO KIDS?
>> I KNOW.
>> SO THAT'S MY PLEA TO YOU
GUYS.
>> YEAH, THANKS FOR COMING OVER.
>> AND I JUST WANTED TO LET YOU
GUYS KNOW THAT'S WHERE MY HEAD'S
AT.
>> THANKS.
>> HEY, MISSY.
>> HI.
>> JOSH APPROACHED JACLYN AND I,
AND SAID,UN," WE WOULD LOVE TO
WORK WITH YOU."
HE PRETTY MUCH SAID,"LOOK, WE
WANT TO GET TO THE FINAL THREE
BUT WE DON'T THINK WE'RE GOING
ON TO ACTUALLY BE THE ONES TO
WIN IT.
ONCE AGAIN WE FIND OURSELVES IN
THE MIDDLE.
IT SEEMS JACLYN AND I BECAME A
POWER COUPLE ONCE THE TRIBE SWAP
HAPPENED.
TWO COUPLES, WE WERE KIND OF IN
THE MIDDLE AND BOTH OF THEM
NEEDED OUR HELP SO WE'RE BEING
GIVEN A LOT OF OPPORTUNITIES TO
CONTROL OUR FATE.
>> THIS VOTE IS HUGE.
>> YEAH, THIS IS THE DECISION.
JOSH AND REED SEEMED
LEGITIMATELY TIED TO KEEPING
COUPLES COULD WOULD GIVE US THE
TOP SIX.
BUT THEY MAKE ( BLEEP ) STUFF
UP.
THEY'RE BROADWAY STARS.
>> IT'S TRUE.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S THE EXACT SAME STORY AGAIN
WITH ME AND JON.
WE ARE FOR SURE IN THE MIDDLE.
SO IT'S, LIKE WHICH WAY DO ME
AND JON GO?
>> THIS IS LIKE A BIG DECISION.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S REALLY STRESSFUL BECAUSE
ONE WRONG VOTE COULD BE A
MILLION-DOLLAR DECISION.
>> I KNOW THAT EVERYBODY IS
LOOKING OUT FOR ANY FOOD THAT'S
JUST LAYING AROUND, AND AT THIS
POINT I STILL HAVE A LITTLE
TRAIL MIX I TOOK FROM FEAST BUT
I'M KEEPING THEM IN MY BAG AND
NOW I FEEL A LITTLE GUILTY.
I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO THROW IT
OUT BECAUSE EVERYBODY HAS
MUNCHED OUT ON EVERYTHING THEY
HAD ALREADY.
IF I SHOWED EVERYBODY WHAT I HAD
IT WOULD BE GONE LIKE THAT.
I WAS SMART ENOUGH TO GATHER IT,
SO IT'S MINE.
>> I HAVE SOME SOME OF THE
LEFTOVER NUTS AND APRICOTS AND
DATES, AND I'LL SHARE WITH WHO I
WANT.
>> WHERE IS JULIE?
>> ON A WALK, I THINK.
OH, YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
>> SHUT UP!
>> YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
>> MISSING TRAIL MIX.
WE FOUND OUT JULIE HAS IT IN HER
BAG, THE SMALLEST GIRL HERE, IT
IS ONE OF THE MOST SELFISH
THINGS YOU COULD DO IN
"SURVIVOR" I FEEL LIKE.
SO A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE PISSED
OFF AT HER FOR THAT, AND WE'RE
PROBABLY GOING TO TAKE IT FROM
HER BAG AND EAT IT ALL.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> BAIL OHURRY, HURRY!
>> GIVE ME SOME!
>> THERE IS SO MUCH IN THERE.
>> I AM BEYOND MAD.
>> WHAT A SELFISH LITTLE-- OOH!
>> AT HOME, OKAY, YOU TAKE TRAIL
MIX, NO BIG DEAL.
IT'S TRAIL MIX.
WHO CARES?
HERE, WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
EAT.
SHE'S SELFISH, AND SHE'S AWFUL,
AND I CAN'T TRUST SOMEBODY IN MY
ALLIANCE WHO IS STEALING
PEOPLE'S FOOD.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> JON, BREATHE.
DEEP BREATHS.
>> IS SHE COMING BACK?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE TO ME.
>> WHY DOES SHE THINK SHE'S SO
MUCH BETTER THAN US AND SHE CAN
DO THAT.
>> IT WAS THE WEIRDEST THING I
WHEN I WALKED BACK UP TO CAMP IT
WAS LITERALLY, LIKE, YOU COULD
SLICE TENSION WITH A KNIFE.
>> I'M A PRETTY OBSERVANT
PERSON.
IT DOESN'T TAKE A BRILLIANT
PERSON TO FIGURE OUT WHAT'S
GOING ON RIGHT HERE.
>> LIKE, SO ENTITLED.
>> I FEEL LIKE SOME OF MY TRIBE
MATES KNOW I WAS HOARDING OR
STEALING TRAIL MIX, AND RIGHT
NOW I FEEL LIKE I'VE GOT A FIRE
UNDER MY BUTT.
SO THINGS DON'T LOOK SO GOOD FOR
ME RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> I'M DEFINITELY IN THE MOST
PRECARIOUS SITUATION I'VE BEEN
IN, IN THIS GAME YET.
WITHOUT JON AND JACLYN ON BOARD,
IT'S STILL NOT A MAJORITY.
I THINK MY NAME WILL BE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK, SO I'M JUST
GOING TO GO OUT THERE AND TRY TO
WIN AND FIGHT TO THE END.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
BAYLOR, TRIBAL IMMUNITY IS NO
MORE.
THIS IS WHAT YOU COVET.
>> SO BEAUTIFUL!
>> Jeff: IT IS BEAUTIFUL.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
WITH THIS AROUND YOUR NECK, ARE
YOU SAFE IN THIS GAME.
WITHOUT IT, YOU COULD BE IN
TROUBLE.
SHALL WE GET TO IT.
>> YES.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU ARE GOING TO
BALANCE A BALL ON A DISK
ATTACHED TO ROPES.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS, YOU WILL
MOVE YOUR HANDS FARTHER BACK ON
THE ROPE MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT TO BALANCE.
AFTER 25 MINUTES, WE WILL ADD A
SECOND BALL.
IF AT ANY POINT YOUR BALL DROPS,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE,
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY LOOKS GOOD.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
THERE'S NOWHERE THAT YOUR BALL
WILL SIT PERFECTLY STILL.
IT IS UP TO YOU TO KEEP IT
STILL.
AND YOU HAVE TWO ROPES.
IF YOU MOVE ONE JUST A LITTLE
MORE THAN THE OTHER, THAT WILL
CAUSE MOVEMENT.
YOU NOT ONLY HAVE TO CONTEND
WITH BALANCING IT.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BATTLE
THE WIND, WHICH COULD COME UP
OUT OF NOWHERE.
JEWEL WEA LITTLE MOVEMENT.
ALEC WITH A LITTLE MOVEMENT.
NICE RECOVERIES.
A LITTLE BIT OF WIND COMING UP.
JEREMY OUT OF NOWHERE, BALL
DROPS, JEREMY OUT, NO SHOOT
IMMUNITY.
THAT'S HOW QUICKLY IT CAN
HAPPEN.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP YOUR
CONCENTRATION.
OVER AND OVER AND OVER AND OVER,
KEEPING REMINDING YOURSELF THIS
ROUND WILL LAST 10 MINUTES.
SURVIVE THIS, MOVE ON TO THE
NEXT ROUND.
O ONE MINUTE LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, MISSY IS OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
JULIE DROPS OUT OF CHALLENGE.
JULIE HAS NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
JACLYN'S BALL IS ON THE MOVE.
ALEC'S BALL IS NOW MOVING.
15 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
JUST HANG ON.
KEEP THAT BALL ON THE DISK.
10 SECONDS LEFT.
FIVE.
FOUR.
THREE.
TWO.
ONE.
EVERYBODY'S SAFE.
YOU CAN DROP YOUR ROPES.
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ROUND.
OKAY, EVERYBODY IS SET FOR THE
SECOND ROUND.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
YOU'RE NOW AT THE FARTHEST END
OF THE ROPE.
YOU'RE ABOUT SIX FEET AWAY FROM
YOUR BALL.
THIS WILL BE THE TOUGHEST PART
OF THE CHALLENGE YET.
A LITTLE WIND COMING UP AGAIN.
THIS IS NOT EASY TO DO.
ESPECIALLY FROM THIS FAR AWAY.
REED'S BALL STARTS TO MOVE.
REED CAN'T RECOVER.
REED IS OUT.
BAYLOR'S BALL-- NICE RECOVERY BY
BAYLOR.
IT'S ON THE MOVE AGAIN.
SHE CAN'T RECOVER THIS TIME.
BAYLOR'S OUT.
ANOTHER GUST OF WIND.
AND THIS GUST OF WIND TAKES ALEC
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
JACLYN'S BALL IS ON THE MOVE.
NICE SAVE BY JACLYN BUT SHE
CAN'T DO IT AGAIN.
JACLYN IS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
ANOTHER GUST OF WIND.
BIG WIND, THE BIGGEST THUS FAR.
NATALIE'S BALL IS MOVING.
HUGE GUST OF WIND.
NATALIE CAN'T DO IT.
NATALIE IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE,
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR.
JOSH, WES, KEITH, AND JON.
EVERYBODY LOOKING VERY STEADY.
10 MINUTES LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
WE WILL ADD A SECOND BALL.
10 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
HANG ON HERE AND YOU MAKE IT TO
THE FINAL PART OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
FIVE SECONDS.
FOUR.
THREE.
TWO.
ONE.
EVERYBODY RELEASE, YOU'RE
SAFE.
GOOD
JOB, GUYS.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY
NOW HAS TWO BALLS ON THEIR DISK.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON AND
IT'S GOING TO GET REALLY TRICKY
VERY QUICKLY.
JOSH JUST LIKE THAT IS OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO THREE.
IT IS WES AND HIS DAD, KEITH,
AND JON.
WITH THE WIND COMING UP AGAIN.
JON'S BALL IS ON THE MOVE.
JON IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO FATHER AND SON.
IT IS KEITH AND WES.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
KEITH, HIS BALL IS ON THE MOVE.
WES' BALL IS ON THE MOVE.
WES STRUGGLING TO HANG IN THERE.
THAT BALL MOVING TOWARD THE
EDGE.
KEITH'S BALL NOW MOVING TOWARD
THE EDGE.
WES IS OUT.
KEITH WINS FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> AWESOME!
>> CRAZY.
>> DUDE, THAT WAS INSANE.
>> YOU BLEW IT!
>> YOU CAN'T EVEN BEAT YOUR OLD
MAN.
>> Jeff: KEITH, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
>> OH, MAN!
ALL RIGHT!
>> Jeff: FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY WIN, SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, CANNOT BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 18
VERY TOUGH DAYS, SOMEBODY GOING
HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANK YOU.
IT'S CRAZY.
I WON IMMUNITY.
IT COME DOWN TO ME AND WESLEY.
I'M NOT READY TO TURN OVER THE
REIGNS TO HIM, BUT TONIGHT IS
CRITICAL.
WE'LL KNOW EXACTLY WHERE
EVERYBODY STANDS AFTER TONIGHT'S
VOTE.
CHALLENGE, FIRST ONE OUT, THIS
IS RIDICULOUS.
I THOUGHT I'D KILL THESE
CHALLENGES.
I'M TERRIBLE AT THESE
>> WELL DONE!
>> WOW!
>> I WAS OUT BEFORE AN OLD GUY.
>> IT WAS FUN TO WATCH YOU AND
YOUR DAD.
>> A MOM.
>> SHE'S REALLY PLAYING HARD,
HUNAHPU.
>> SHE'S OVER THERE TANNING.
>> JEWEL-- I WAS OUT BEFORE
JULIE.
I WAS OUT BEFORE JULIE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
BUT GOING INTO THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT, I FEEL LIKE I'M
SAFE.
I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
>> OH, BABY I KNOW.
I HEAR YA.
>> IT'S SO HOT.
I CAN'T EVEN DRINK IT YET.
>> I SURE WOULD LOVE THE TRAIL
MIX.
>> I HEARD ALEC'S LITTLE PUNK
BUTT SAYING SOMETHING ABOUT
TRAIL MIX.
I'M DEFINITELY ANGRY, BUT I
DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
I'M JUST-- I'M REALLY LOST.
I'M FEELING REALLY LOW.
I'M FEELING LOST AND CONFUSED.
>> THE PAST THREE, FOUR DAYS
I'VE JUST KIND OF, LIKE-- IT'S
JUST TOUGH.
I FEEL LIKE I'M NOT-- I'M ALMOST
EVERY NIGHT NOT QUITE ABLE TO
GET MY HEAD BACK IN THE GAME.
I DON'T KNOW-- I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU FEEL LIKE YICY.
>> A LITTLE BIT.
>> YOU FEEL LIKE DONE.
>> ALMOST.
>> TOAST?
REMEMBER YOU HAD A TOUGHER TIME
THAN OTHER PEOPLE BECAUSE JOHN
GOT VOTED OUT SUPER EARLY.
>> IT IS DIFFICULT WITH ALL THIS
HERE WHEN EVERYBODY HAS THEIR
LOVED ONE.
>> I KNOW.
WELL, I'M YOUR LOVED ONE.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
>> HANG IN THERE.
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
BECAUSE I'M A LITTLE-- I'M NOT
SURE.
MY HEAD'S KIND OF TELLING ME
TO--
>> GET OUT?
>> YEAH.
>> DON'T DO IT YET.
>> JUST BECAUSE I KNOW THERE'S
SO MUCH MORE TO ENDURE.
>> THERE IS.
>> I FEEL LIKE IF I DON'T GET A
LITTLE SPACE I'M GOING TO LOSE
MY ( BLEEP ) MIND.
>> SHE STOLE FOOD AND PUT
IT IN HER BAG AND DIDN'T SHARE
WITH ANYBODY AND IT'S OBNOXIOUS,
IT IS.
JULIE GOES HOME AND IT MESSES US
UP.
ONE MESS-UP VOTE AT TRIBAL
THROWS THIS PLAN INTO THE
TOILET.
LET'S NOT DO IT TONIGHT.
CAN YOU WAIT ONE MORE DAY?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN WE GET THROUGH THIS PLAN?
>> I NEEDED TO TALK TO SOMEBODY.
I FELT LIKE I COULD TALK TO
MISSY, BUT WHEN SHE TOLD ME TO
STICK IT OUT, "I'M HERE FOR YOU.
I'M YOUR LOVED ONE.
I'M YOUR LOVED ONE WHEN JOHN'S
GONE.
JUST DO THIS.
WE NEED YOU."
>> OKAY?
>> YEAH, HUGS.
I GET IT.
I'M A SMART GAL.
THEY NEED ME TO GET FURTHER
BASED ON USING ME.
I'M NOT GOING TO HATE THEM FOR
IT.
IT'S THE WAY THE GAME GOES.
I CAN SEE WHAT THAT IS AND I CAN
MAKE A DECISION RIGHT NOW BASED
ON WHAT I NEED.
>> THEY'RE STILL AFTER YOU HARD
CORE.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE PRETENDING
JULIE, BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> WHAT'S THEIR REASONING TO SAY
ME?
>> THEY SAID YOU'RE GOING TO WIN
ALL OF THE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES.
>> DON'T THEY KNOW-- I SUCK AT
THESE IMMUNITY CHALLENGES?
LIKE I'M OUT FIRST,UN WHAT I
MEAN?
>> YEAH, YOU WERE.
>> THEY'RE JUST MAKING STUFF UP.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
>> BUT THEY DON'T HAVE NUMBERS,
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> YEAH IT, DOESN'T MATTER.
>> JOSH IS THE ONLY ONE IN
JOSH' ALLIANCE THAT IS PLAYING
THE GAME.
IF YOU TAKE HIM OUT, IT'S OVER.
>> WE JUST GO ON JOSH.
THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY HAS BEEN
SAYING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THIS IS MY HOME TURF.
BUT I HAVE TO GIVE JEREMY PROPS
BECAUSE HE IS PLAYING THIS GAME,
AND ACTUALLY, HE'S PLAYING IT
WELL.
IT JUST IS OPPOSITE TO WHAT I'M
DOING, SO IT'S FRUSTRATING.
>> HI.
>> WE HAVE TO GET JACLYN AND
JON.
IT WOULD MAKE SENSE TO GO
COUPLES TOGETHER AND SINGLES
OUT.
BLOOD VERSUS WATER.
THAT'S WHAT THIS GAME IS ABOUT.
WHY DON'T WE GET RID OF THE
PEOPLE WHO DON'T HAVE THEIR
LOVED ONES ANYMORE?
>> WE DON'T STICK TOGETHER AND
JEREMY-- IF HE GETS FIVE VOTES
AND DOESN'T GET VOTEDDED OFF
HE'S GOIN TO BE PISSED AND
COMING AFTER EVERY ONE OF US.
>> AND JEREMY IS GOING TO BE
TAKE OUT THE COUPLES.
>> IS HE.
>> AND WE ALSO GET TO BE HERE
WITH OUR LOVED ONE AND HAVING A
LOVED ONE MAKES IT MORE OF A
CALM RAWDY THING.
THEN ONCE WE GET IT DOWN TO
EIGHT WE'LL DUKE IT OUT.
>> I'M IN.
>> I LOVE THIS PLAN.
>> AFTER LOOKING AT THE OPTIONS,
FEELING OUT THE PEOPLE, I'VE
FOUND MYSELF MAKING A COMPLETE
180 IN TERMS OF WHAT ALLIANCES
I AM SUPPORTING.
>> THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT, I
JUST CAN'T TRUST JEREMY.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING WITH HIM?
>> NO.
WE'LL GET JEREMY OUT TONIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> BLINDSIDE HIM.
>> ARE WE REALLY?
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE THAT'S HUGE.
>> WHAT.
>> THAT WE'RE GOING THE OTHER
WAY NOW.
>> I DON'T EVEN WANT TO JUMP,
IT'S JUST THE BEST THING FOR OUR
GAME.
>> ANOTHER I FEEL GOOD ABOUT
THAT, YEAH.
OKAY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GOING TO
BE GOING ON THE COUPLES TRAIN,
AND VOTING JEREMY OUT TONIGHT.
IT'S GOING TO SUCK BECAUSE I
REALLY LIKE JEREMY, BUT WE'VE
GOT TO DO, THIS WE GOTTA DO IT.
>> THAT SUCTION.
>> YUP.
I PREACHED AGAINST JUMPING SHIP
BEFORE BECAUSE IF YOU JUMP SHIP
YOU'RE GOING TO BE ON THE BOTTOM
OF THE TOTEM POLE, BUT WE ARE A
COUPLE.
SO I'M GOING WITH JOSH, REED,
ALEC, WES, AND KEITH HAS MORE
LONG-TERM POTENTIAL WITH FEWER
BUMPS IN THE ROAD.
>> WHERE'S JULIE?
>> WITH HER BAG.
SHE WALKED THAT WAY.
>> I THINK SHE TOTALLY HEARD ME
JUST HATING ON HER.
>> SHE DEFINITELY HEARD YOU.
>> WELL, IT NEEDED TO HAPPEN.
SOMEBODY NEEDED TO SAY IT, SO I
DID IT.
YOU GUYS ALL THOUGHT IT, AND I
SAID IT.
>> DAMN IT.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE'LL QUIT.
SHE TOLD ME SHE WOULDN'T QUIT,
SHOW.
SHE SAID SHE WOULDN'T WOULDN'T.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT IN MY WILDEST
DREAMS THAT BLOOD VERSUS WATER
WOULD BE THIS DIFFICULT.
IT HAS BEEN THE LONGEST THREE
WEEKS OF MY LIFE AWAY FROM THE
MAN I LOVE.
AND IT'S, LIEB, TAKING A TOLL ON
ME.
HEY, JEFF.
THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> UM, I'VE KIND OF LOST MY HEAD
THE PAST THREE, FOUR DAYS, AND
I'VE BEEN TRYING MY BEST TO
REGROUP AND SHAKE MY HEAD BACK
IN BUT I HAVEN'T QUITE GOT BACK
THERE.
AND TO BE HERE WITH ALL OF THESE
COUPLES, IT BRINGS ME RIGHT BACK
TO I WAS DOING THIS WHOLE THING
WITH JOHN.
AND BEING HERE WITH ALL OF THESE
PEOPLE THAT ARE IN LOVE, ARE
FAMILY MEMBERS, IT'S-- IT'S THAT
MUCH MORE DIFFICULT ON TOP OF
EVERYTHING ELSE THAT'S
HAPPENING.
>> Jeff: TELL ME ABOUT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH JOHN.
ARE YOU GUYS ALWAYS TOGETHER?
>> THIS SUMMER'S THREE YEARS,
AND WE HAVE NOT GONE MORE THAN
FOUR DAYS WITHOUT SEEING EACH
GLRG SO YOU'RE IN A RELATIONSHIP
IN WHICH BEING APART IS JUST NOT
WHAT WE DO, AND SO SUDDENLY THE
THOUGHT OF BEING OUT HERE
ANOTHER 21 DAYS IS--
>> HEAVY.
>> Jeff: OVERWHELMING.
>> OVERWHELMING IS THE WORD.
>> Jeff: BUT KIDS GO TO SUMMER
CAMP LONGER THAN WE'RE OUT HERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: THEY LEAVE THEIR
PARENTS.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: PARENTS LET THEIR
KIDS GO.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: WE KNOW THAT WE CAN
LEAVE PEOPLE THAT WE LOVE.
>> SURE, SURE.
>> Jeff: SO IS PART OF THIS
THAT YOU FEEL YOU'RE ALREADY OUT
OF THE GAME?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE FOR PEOPLE
TO SAY JULIE, IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE GIVING UP BECAUSE YOU
THINK YOU'RE OUT AND YOU JUST
WANT TO BE WITH JOHN.
>> I CAME IN HERE DAY ONE BEING
JUDGED.
I'M JUDGED CONSTANTLY.
>> Jeff: WHY DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE JUDGED SO QUICKLY?
>> MAYBE THEY SEE ME AS SOMEBODY
THEY CAN'T APPROACH, OR SOMEBODY
THEY CAN'T TRUST BECAUSE I TAKE
CARE OF MYSELF.
MAYBE IT SEEMS I WOULDN'T BE
DOWN TO EARTH, MAYBE TOO VAIN.
AND THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT MY
BOOBS, LIKE MAKING JOKES, LIKE
MEAN GIRLS.
>> Jeff: SO THE FACT THAT YOU
THINK YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH ON THE
VERGE OF BEING VOTE OUT AND YOUR
MAN'S NOT HERE-- I'M DONE.
>> AND I CAN'T STAY HERE BECAUSE
MISSY SAYS, "WE NEED YOU."
I KNOW WHY YOU NEED ME.
IT'S BECAUSE YOU WANT ME TO BE
HERE TO HELP YOU GET FURTHER IN
THE GAME.
BUT I'M COMPROMISING WHAT I FEEL
I NEED RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: AND WHAT ABOUT PEOPLE
ROWHOARE IN AN ALLIANCE WITH YOU
AND THE FACT IF THEY ARE, THEY
JUST LOST A MEMBER JAI FEEL VERY
BUILT ABOUT THAT, I DO.
>> Jeff: IT IS QUITE POSSIBLY
A MILLION-DOLLAR QUIT FOR
SOMEONE ELSE.
>> IT MAKES ME FEEL AWFUL BUT I
CANNOT COMPROMISE WHAT I'M
NEEDING RIGHT NOW BASED ON WHAT
THEY NEED BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
THEM.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JULIE.
SO OFFICIALLY, YOU'RE QUITTING
THE GAME.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
18 DAYS, YOUR ADVENTURE IS OVER.
I'LL GO LET THE TRIBE KNOW.
>> ANOTHER THANK YOU.
>> OKAY, SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
>> Jeff: GUYS, COME ON DOWN
OUT OF THE SHELTER.
THERE'S A LOG UP HERE.
LET'S JUST SIT ON THIS.
ALL RIGHT, SO, BAD NEWS AND GOOD
NEWS.
BAD NEWS IS IF YOU WERE IN AN
ALLIANCE WITH JULIE, YOU JUST
LOST A MEMBER.
JULIE IS QUITTING THE GAME.
>> WOW.
>> AS SOON AS JEFF SAYS JULIE'S
GONE, I INSTANTLY THINK ABOUT
THE NUMBERS.
SHE WAS MY NUMBER.
I NEEDED THAT.
SO NOW I COULD BE GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> HOW CAN SOMEBODY DO THAT?
>> Jeff: SOME PEOPLE
DISAPPOINTED, SOME PEOPLE
SMILING.
>> I'M JUST SAD BECAUSE I TALKED
TO HER LAST TODAY.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T TAKE ANY
RESPONSIBILITY FOR IT BUT I WISH
I COULD HAVE TALKED TO HER ONE
MORE TIME.
>> Jeff: JOSH, IT'S A
COMPLICATED GAME.
ON ONE HAPPENED, YOU DON'T WANT
SOMEBODY TO QUIT, ESPECIALLY IF
YOU'RE THE PERSON THAT'S IN AN
ALLIANCE WITH THEM.
ON THE OTHER HAND, MY ODDS JUST
GOT BETTER BY ONE.
>> IT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
YOUR CHANCES JUST GOT BETTER IN
THAT CASE, UNLESS SHE WAS YOUR
ONLY ALLIANCE, AND THEN, OF
COURSE, MAYBE YOU THINK YOU'RE
SCREWED AFTER THAT.
JULIE QUIT THE GAME, WHICH PUTS
JEREMY AND THAT ALLIANCE A
LITTLE MORE AT AN EASE BECAUSE
THEY HAVE ONE LESS NUMBER.
AND I'M HAPPY ABOUT THAT BECAUSE
OUR ODDS ARE BETTER AT TRIBAL
TONIGHT TO GET JEREMY OUT.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, WHAT DOES IT
SAY ABOUT THOSE WHO JUST GIVE
UP?
>> IT'S RIDICULOUS.
AND IT PISSES ME OFF WHEN PEOPLE
QUIT AS IT IS YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN?
WE'RE TRYING TO MAKE HER
COMFORTABLE AND GIVE HER FOOD,
KEEP HER WARM AT NIGHT.
IT'S JUST RIDICULOUS.
IT'S--
>> AND IT SEEMS LIKE JULIE HAD
LIFE THE EASIEST OF ANYBODY
AROUND HERE BECAUSE SHE DID
NOTHING.
YOU KNOW?
SO--
>> SHE DUG HERSELF A BIT OF A
HOLE.
>> SHE DUG HERSELF NAY HOLE.
>> Jeff: DO YOU THINK, JACLYN,
PARENT OF THE REASON SHE QUIT IS
SHE FELT SHE WAS IN A HOLE?
>> YEAH, IT PROBABLY HAD A BIG
PART.
AFTER THE MERGE FEAST WE HAD,
SHE DUMP AID BUNCH OF TRAIL MIX
IN HER BAG AND HID IT FROM
EVERYBODY AND WE FOUND IT TODAY.
I MEAN, FOOD IS HUGE OUT HERE,
AND IF YOU JUST, LIKE, TAKE
SOMETHING AND HIDE IT FROM
EVERYBODY AND KEEP IT IT TO
YOURSELF, LIKE, IT MAKES PEOPLE
MAD.
>> Jeff: SO, JON, DO YOU THINK
PART OF THIS MIGHT BE SHE FEARED
SHE WAS GOING HOME?
>> I THINK EVEN MORE SO IT'S
THAT SHE WAS JUST SO SCARED OF
LIVING UP TO THE FACT THAT, OH,
YEAH, I AM A SELFISH PERSON.
I DON'T THINK SHE COULD DEAL
WITH IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THERE IS
GOOD NEWS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHICH MEANS, SOMEBODY MAYBE JUST
GOT A MILLION-DOLLAR BREAK.
GUYS, HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
I HOPE YOU STAY DRY.
THE GAME CONTINUES.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
>> I DO FEEL LIKE WITH JULIE'S
EARLY EXIT, IT WAS NOT ON OUR
SIDE BECAUSE WE WANTED TO GET
JEREMY OUT RIGHT THEN, AND THAT
PLAN WAS SOLID, IT SEEMED LIKE.
BUT JEREMY HOPEFULLY IS ON
BORROWED TIME RIGHT NOW, AND I
DON'T THINK HE EVEN REALIZED.
I THINK HE THINKS REED OR MYSELF
WOULD BE GONE TODAY, AND THERE
WAS A 20% CHANCE OF THAT
HAPPENING, BUT I THINK THERE WAS
AN 80% CHANCE OF JEREMY LEAVING.
>> YEAH, JULIE KIND OF MESSED IT
UP.
I WANTED JOSH OUT OF THE GAME.
I FEEL LIKE IT BOTHERED ME MORE
THAN ANYBODY ELSE.
I'M REALLY UPSET THAT SHE LEFT
BECAUSE SHE REALLY MESSED UP MY
PLANS.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> YOU WANT SOME FISH?
I MEAN, THIS AIN'T NO CHARITY
NOW.
>> Jeff: IT'S THE I BATTLE OF
THE SEXES AND IT HITS JON AND
JACKLIN THE HARDEST.
>> WHY.
>> JON JUST DOESN'T CARE.
>> JACLYN IS NOT ON THE SAME
PAGE AS I AM.
>> SOMEBODY IS NOT GOING TO BE
HAPPY.
>> THIS HAS BEEN MENTALLY
EXHAUSTING AND I THINK I WILL
HAVE TO DEAL WITH A LOT OF
BACKLASH BUT I WAS THE ONE HERE
I WAS THE ONE CLOSE TO
DEHYDRATION.
I WAS THE ONE MISSING MY LOVED
ONES WITH NO COMMUNICATION FOR
THREE WEEKS.
ONLY I KNOW HOW TOUGH THIS WAS
ON ME.