>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": EIGHTH PERSON VOTED
OUT AND SECOND MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
JEREMY AFTER REED WATCHED THE
MAJORITY ALLIANCE TURN ON ONE OF
THEIR ORGANIC HE SAW AN
OPPORTUNITY TO FLIP THE GAME.
USING EASTERN ON THE BOTTOM.
>> AS LONG AS WE CAN STICK
TOGETHER AND DON'T TURN ON ONE
ANOTHER, WE'LL FIGURE SOMETHING
OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: REED CONVINCED THE
MAJORITY ALLIANCE TO SPLIT THEIR
VOTES.
BUT HIS REAL PLAN WAS TO VOTE
OUT JON, TEAMING UP WITH ALEC,
WES, AND KEITH.
>> JON?
>> YES.
>> IT'S AN AMAZING PLAN BUT IT
HAS TO BE STUCK TO.
>> Jeff: BUT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, NOTHING WENT RIGHT.
>> I SAY STICK TO THE PLAN.
( LAUGHS )
THAT'S ALL I CAN SAY.
>> Jeff: WOW.
KEITH GAVE AWAY THEIR PLAN.
>> JEFF, I'D RATHER PLAY THIS
THAN GO HOME WITH IT IN MY
POCKET.
>> Jeff: TWO IDOLS WERE
PLAYED.
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: AND KEITH'S SON, WES,
WAS VOTED OUT.
WES, YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
>> SLY DOG, YOU.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: WES, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
EIGHT ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS CRAZY.
IT DIDN'T GO QUITE AS WE
ANTICIPATED, AND WESLEY WENT
HOME.
>> HE PANICKED, AND HE PLAYED
THE IDOL.
>> HOW DID HE KNOW THAT WAS THE
PLAN?
>> I'M PISSED AT KEITH.
KEITH GAVE US AWAY TONIGHT.
HE'S NOT VERY GOOD AT TRIBAL,
AND NOW I FEEL COMPLETELY
HELPs.
>> MY ALLIANCE MEANS NOTHING.
WE DON'T HAVE THE NUMBERS.
AND I DON'T TRUST REED AT ALL.
>> THEY'RE OVER THERE PLOTTING
THEIR REVENGE RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE THAN ANGRY
GIRLS.
>> THAT WAS THE BEST BLINDS SIDE
SNIFF-OUT EVER.
>> HE WAS NOT GOING TO PLAY HIS
IDOL, I WAS LIKE, " WHY O, PLAY
YOUR IDOL.
>> I'M GLAD YOU WERE SITTING
THERE.
>> I WAS LIKE, "JON, PLAY IT,
PLAY IT."
>> I WAS GOING TO PLAY IT.
I WAS GOING TO PLAY IT.
>> NO, YOU WEREN'T, YOU WEREN'T
GOING TO PLAY IT.
>> I WAS GOING TO PLAY IT.
>> JON SAID HE WAS GOING TO PLAY
THE IDOL WHICH WAS TOTAL BULL
CRAP.
I CONVINCED HIM TO PLAY IT.
JON IS SO CONCERNED WITH LOOKING
LIKE HE'S THE MASTERS MIND OF
WHAT HE DOES BUT HE'S NOT AT
ALL.
>> WHO?
>> YOU'RE LIKE, "I'M SO GLAD
THAT YOU TOLD JON TO PLAY THE
IDOL.
OF.
>> NATALIE?
>> YEAH.
LIKE, WHEN WE TALK ABOUT IT
LATER.
THE JURY NEEDS TON I SAID--
>> WHO'S THE JURY?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
LIKE WHO IS SITTING RIGHT HERE?
>> WHEN I'M IN THE TOP THREE--
>> OKAY, WELL, WHAT HAPPENS IF I
GET IN THE TOP THREE AND YOU
DON'T.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> SO STOP ACTING LIKE YOU ARE
GOING TO--
>> BABE.
I'M-- I'M-- I'M-- I--
>> OKAY, BUT I FEEL--
>> I'LL DO ANYTHING I CAN TO
HELP YOUR CASE.
>> I FEEL LIKE THAT'S THE
SMALLEST THING YOU'RE POINTING
OUT TO ME RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S THE SMALLEST THING.
>> JACLYN GAVE NATALIE THE PROPS
FOR MY PLAY.
WE NEED THIS FOR JURY.
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT WAS HER PLAY,
THEN SHE'S GOING TO USE IT.
WE CAN'T DO THAT THP THAT'S
TERRIBLE.
BABE, WHY ARE YOU FREAKING OUT?
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE LIKE GIVE ME
ALL THE WHEN IT WAS ME AND
NATALIE HELPING YOU WITH THAT
DECISION JIERVETION SAYING DON'T
GIVE IT TO NATALIE.
>> I WAS SO MAD WHEN HE TOOK
CREDIT FOR SOMETHING THAT I
HELPED HIM DO, THAT HE WAS LIKE,
"STOP SAYING YOU HELPED AND
NATALIE HELPED.
IT WAS MY DECISION."
I WAS LIKE, SCREW YOU.
I'M GOING TO THE TOP THREE THEN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, WE'RE GOING TO SEE
HOW WELL YOU KNOW YOUR
TRIBEMATES.
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU A SERIES OF
QUESTIONS ABOUT THE PEOPLE IN
THIS GAME.
GET ONE RIGHT, YOU GET TO CHOP
ANOTHER PERSON'S ROPE.
ONCE YOUR ROPE HAS BEEN CHOPPED
THREE TIMES, YOU'RE OUT OF THE
GAME.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YES!
>>, OF COURSE!
>> Jeff: THE WINNER UPON SPEND
THE ARCH ON HORSES BACK THROUGH
THE COUNTRYSIDE OF SAN JUAN DEL
SUR.
THE RIDE WILL CONCLUDE AT A
BEAUTIFUL RESORT WHERE YOU WILL
ENJOY A NICE MEAL OF BARBECUED
BEEF, BARBECUED CHICKEN,
BROWNIES.
>> AAHH!
>> Jeff: YOU'LL SPEND THE
NIGHT AND RETURN TO CAMP IN THE
MORNING.
>> OH, MY GOD!
HORSES AND BROWNIES!
>> Jeff: WORTH PLAYING FOR,
BAYLOR?
>> OH, YEAH!
>> YES!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'RE
GOING TO DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
ALL OF THESE QUESTIONS PERTAIN
TO PEOPLE WHO WERE IN THE GAME
POST-MERGE, GOT IT.
>> GOT IT.
>> FROM JULIE DOWN.
>> Jeff: FIRST QUESTION,
NATALIE AND NADIYA ARE TWINS.
WHO ELSE HAS A TWIN SIBLING?
GO BACK TO BACK WHILE YOU'RE
WRITING YOUR ANSWERS SO NOBODY
CAN SEE.
WHEN YOU HAVE IT, TURN AROUND,
KEEP IT TOWARDS YOUR CHEST.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY REVEAL.
EVERYBODY SAYS JEREMY, EXCEPT
KEITH, WHO SAYS JAX.
WHO'S JAX?
>> JACLYN.
>> Jeff: OH, JACLYN.
JEREMY IS THE CORRECT ANSWER.
EVERYBODY GOT IT RIGHT EXCEPT
KEITH.
TAKE A STEPED FOR IF YOU GOT IT
RIGHT.
NATALIE, YOU WERE UP FIRST, YOU
CAN CHOP ANYBODY'S ROPE YOU
WANT.
>> GOOD FOR REED, REED.
>> Jeff: NATALIE GOING AFTER
REED.
RIGHT AWAY.
REED TAKES HIS FIRST HIT.
THREE HITS AND YOU'RE OUT OF
THIS GAME.
JON UP NEXT.
>> THIS IS BRUTAL.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES THAT
FAMED, "OH, I HATE TO DO THIS."
REED TAKE HIS SECOND HIT.
THINGS NOT LOOKING GOOD FOR REED
GOING ON A HORSES BACK RIDE.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT, MY FAMILY
HAS 12.
>> Jeff:
>> OH, MY!
>> Jeff: ALEC, YOU'RE UP.
ALEC HEADING SOMEWHERE NEW.
ALEC GIVES NATALIE HER FIRST HIT
WITH SOME AUTHORITY.
MISSY, YOU'RE UP.
THE GAME IS GETTING PERSONAL
EARLY.
MISSY GOING TO PUT REED OUT OF
HIS MISERY.
AND WITH THAT--
>> OH!
>> Jeff: VERY SYMBOLIC IN
"BLOOD VERSUS WATER" THAT REED
IS NOW COVERED IN BLOOD, HIS
SKULL CRUSHED, NO SHOT IN THIS
GAME.
JACLYN, YOU'RE UP.
JACLYN GIVES ALEC HIS FIRST HIT.
>> I SAW THAT ONE COMING.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, YOU'RE UP.
BAYLOR GIVES ALEC A SECOND HIT.
REED, YOU STILL GET A HIT
BECAUSE YOU GOT IT RIGHT.
REED IT OUT OF THE GAME BUT HE
GETS ONE CHOP AND HE GIVES IT TO
MISSY.
WHY MISSY?
>> SHE CRUSHED MY SKULL.
>> Jeff: REED, FIRST PERSON
OUT, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
NEXT QUESTION: WHO OWNS AND
OPERATES THEIR OWN TANNING
BUSINESS?
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
EVERYBODY SAYS JULIE.
EVERYBODY GOT IT RIGHT.
JON, YOU'RE UP.
YOU GOT RID OF REED.
NOW WHO YOU GOING AFTER?
JON DOESN'T HESITATE.
ALEC OUT OF THIS GAME.
ALEC GOT IT RIGHT.
HE WILL STILL GET A SHOT.
A CHANCE FOR A LITTLE PAYBACK.
>> YUP.
ALEC HEADS TO JON.
WITH THAT, ALEC IS OUT OF THE
GAME.
MISSY, YOU'RE UP.
MISSY GOING AFTER KEITH.
JACLYN, YOU'RE UP.
WITH THAT, KEITH GETS ANOTHER
HIT FROM JACLYN.
KEITH.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> WHO KNOWS?
>> Jeff: MISSY TAKES HER
SECOND HIT.
BAYLOR, YOU'RE UP.
BAYLOR COULD PUT KEITH OUT OF IT
RIGHT HERE.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: KEITH ALREADY HEADING
OVER.
HE KNOWS IT'S COMING.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: SHE'S TAKES A VICIOUS
SMASH.
>> DISGUSTING.
>.>> Jeff: THAT WAS BRUTAL.
>> SHOWS YOU WHERE WE STAND,
DOESN'T IT?
>> WHAT DO WE WANT TO DO.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF TALKING
GOING ON OVER THERE, ALEC.
>> YOU GUYS HAVE HAD TWO.
>> I'LL GO.
>> YOU HAVEN'T BEEN TO ONE YET.
>> THEY HAVEN'T BEEN TO ONE YET.
>> Jeff: LET ME ASK YOU GUYS A
QUESTION.
IS THIS GOING TO BE A FRIENDLY,
WE'RE JUST GOING TO SEE HOW THIS
GOES BETWEEN OF FIVE OF YOU FOR
THE REST OF THIS CHALLENGE?
>> PROBABLY SO.
>> PROBABLY.
>> Jeff: WHY ARE WE WASTING
OUR TIME?
I THINK THIS IS JUST A BIG
CHARADE, AND IF REALLY ALL THIS
IS WE'RE JUST THROWING IT UNTIL
WE GET THE PERSON WE WANT TO
WIN, TELL ME WHO IT'S GOING TO
BE.
>> PROBABLY MY MOM IS GOING TO
WIN.
>> I'M GOING TO WIN.
>> MISSY.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY ELSE OVER
HERE.
MISSY, COME OVER TO ME.
FIRST TIME EVER--
>> LET'S PLAY FOR FUN.
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
>> A FIVE-SOME IS JUST GOING TO
GIVE IT TO SOMEBODY.
THE FIVE SAID LET'S FIGURE IT
OUT AND THEY WANT YOU TO WIN.
SO WE'LL END THE CHALLENGE.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> Jeff: THAT'S FINE.
EVERYBODY IS GOOD WITH THIS.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE NOW.
THE FIRST THING YOU HAVE TO DO
BEFORE YOU GO ON YOUR HORSES
BACK RIDE IS DECIDE WHO GOES TO
EXILE ISLAND, AND YOU ALREADY
HAVE A VOLUNTEER.
>> I'M GOING TO SEND JON.
>> Jeff: JON YOU KNOW THE WAY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD OUT.
ALL RIGHT, MISSY, NOW YOU HAVE A
TOUGH DECISION.
YOU'RE BRINGING TWO PEOPLE ON
THIS REWARD.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO CHOOSE TO GO
WITH YOU?
>> BAYLOR.
>> Jeff: DAUGHTER'S COMING TO
JOIN MOMMA.
NOW, YOU HAVE ONE CHOICE LEFT,
BASED ON WHAT WE JUST SAW IT
WOULD SEEM THAT IT WOULD BE
JACLYN OR NATALIE.
ONE'S GOING TO JOIN YOU, ONE
WILL STAY BACK WITH ALEC, REED,
AND KEITH.
WHAT A FUN NIGHT THAT WILL BE.
>> OKAY, NATALIE, COME.
>> IT'S OKAY, GIRL.
YOU HAVE TWO DATES WITH YOUR
BOO, RIGHT, I AIN'T GOT NOW BOO
OUT HERE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, HARD?
>> YEAH, BUT I SAW IT COMING.
THOSE THREE ARE TIGHT.
>> Jeff: A MOMENT AGO IT WAS A
HAPPY FIVE, SO HAPPY YOU SAID
GIVE IT TO MISSY.
AND NOW HERE WE SIT, JON GOING
TO EXILE,URE AND GOING BACK TO
CAMP AND RICE WITH THREE PEOPLE
WHO PROBABLY DON'T LIKE YOU VERY
MUCH.
>> WE LIKE HER A LOT.
>> I'M SURE YOU DO.
>> YOU LIKE EVERYBODY, REED.
>> PAUSE I'M A PEOPLE PERSON,
BAYLOR.
YOU'RE A BRAT.
>> EXCUSE ME?
DID YOU JUST CALL HER A BRAT?
>> SHE'S BEING A BRAT.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: SO, MISSY, GAME JUST
GOT VERY PERSONAL FUR.
>> SURE.
THAT'S MY KID.
>> I KNOW IT'S YOUR KID.
>> SHE'S NOT A GIRL, SHE'S A
MOM.
>> THAT'S FINE, I UNDERSTAND
SHE'S YOUR MOM.
BUT YOU'RE-- HOW OLD ARE YOU,
20-SOMETHING?
IF YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A BRAT,
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU, YOU'RE
BEING A BRAT RIGHT NOW.
>> REED.
>> MISSY.
>> YOU'VE BEEN AFTER EVERYBODY
IN THIS GAME--
>> HOW HAVE I BEEN AFTER
EVERYONE.
>> WHY DON'T YOU LISTEN FOR ONE
ONCE, SHUT YOUR MOUTH FOR ONCE
AND I WILL TELL YOU.
I HAVE HAD YOUR BACK MULTIPLE
TIMES.
>> YOU HAVE NOT.
>> YOU LIED TO MY FACE.
>> IT'S THE GAME, OF COURSE, I'M
GOING TO LIE TO YOU.
>> FORGET IT.
IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
>>
>> Jeff: FORGET IT?
>> IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
HE CAN'T LISTEN.
HE DOESN'T KNOW HOW.
>> Jeff: MISSY, BAYLOR,
NATALIE, HORSES BACK RIDING,
RESORT, GREAT MEAL, GOOD NIGHT'S
SLEEP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, AND
ENJOY IT.
>> HANG IN THERE, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> COME ON, GIRLS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> I FEEL LIKE JON SACRIFICED
FOR OUR ALLIANCE, AND I GOT THE
BUTT END.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> AND THE THREE TOP PEOPLE JUST
WENT OFF TO GO HORSES BACK
RIDING.
THAT'S HONESTLY HOW I FEEL.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT JUST
HAPPENED.
>> THAT'S HOW YOU SHOULD FEEL.
THEM THREE RIGHT THERE ARE
TIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JACLYN,
ALEC, REED, KEITH, GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> IT WAS VERY TELLING.
MISSY CHOSE NATALIE.
THAT MAKES ME THINK THAT WHEN
ITS DOES DOES COME DOWN TO OUR
FIVE IT WOULD BE BAYLOR, MISSY,
AND NATALIE.
IT MAKES ME SECOND GUESS
EVERYTHING.
EXILE BECAUSE THERE WERE TWO
IDOLS PLAYED LAST NIGHT, AND
THERE WAS GOING TO BE A NEW CLUE
FOR A NEW IDOL, SO FINDING THIS
IDOL IS SOMETHING THAT'S
DEFINITELY GOING TO HELP ME.
"SIDEWAYS TREE MARKS THE WAY TO
THE TREASURE YOU CRAVE THE MOST.
IT'S A DRIER TREK AT LEAST TWICE
A DAY SO ENJOY A STROLL ALONG
THE COAST."
HAVING A LOT OF TIME ON EXILE
GIVES YOU A LOT OF TIME TO
THINK, AND RIGHT NOW, MY FEAR IN
THIS GAME IS THAT I'VE BECOME
THE BIGGEST THREAT, AND THAT'S
SCARY BECAUSE PEOPLE TRY TO GET
OUT THE LARGEST THREATS, SO I AM
NOT GOING TO STOP UNTIL I FIND
THE DANG THING.
"SIDEWAYS TREE MARKS THE WAY."
I'M LOOKING AROUND AND I SEE
CLIFFS ALL OVER THE PLACE, AND
THERE ARE TREES HANGING OFF OF
THEM, JUST SHOOTING OUT.
"IT'S A DRIER TREK AT LEAST
TWICE A DAY."
IT'S NOT DRY RIGHT NOW.
I SAW A BUNCH OF SIDEWAYS TREES,
AND I STARTED SEEING A LOT OF
CRACKS AND CREVICES.
SO I WAS THINKING, YOU KNOW,
THIS LOOKS LIKE THE PERFECT
PLACE TO HIDE AN IDOL.
THERE'S THE TREE.
YES!
HA-HA-HA!
OH, MAN!
I LOVE THIS!
FINDING THIS IDOL IS SOMETHING
THAT'S DEFINITELY GOING TO HELP
ME AND REFOCUS ME EVEN MORE ON
JACLYN AND I'S FUTURE.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
>> WHAT A PERFECT DAY!
>> THIS IS THE PERFECT REWARD
FOR US TO ENJOY TOGETHER.
RIDING HORSES WAS AMAZING.
ME GOT TO SEE NICARAGUA FROM
ANOTHER VIEW.
WE WEREN'T STUCK ON THE BEACH
ANYMORE.
WE WERE TAKING IT ALL IN.
IT WAS ABSOLUTELY MAGNIFICENT.
I DON'T THINK I'LL EVER FORGET
THE EXPERIENCE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WE'RE AT A PALACE!
>> I WANT TO SEE THE FOOD AND
THE POOL!
THIS IS AMAZING.
SALAD, CHIPS, BEANS.
>> YOU GUYS, THIS IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
MISSY, THANKS SO MUCH FOR
PICKING ME.
>> MOM, THANKS FOR TAKING YOUR
DAUGHTER.
>> TO HAVE BAYLOR AND ME
TOGETHER WAS FANTASTIC, AND TO
HAVE NATALIE ALONG WHO REALLY
ADOARS MY DAUGHTER AS A BIG
SISTER KIND OF TYPE, SHE'LL BE
LIKE A DAUGHTER TO ME FOREVER.
>> TO THE GIRLS.
>> I COULDN'T HAVE GONE ON THAT
REWARD WITH ANYBODY ELSE AND HAD
THAT SAME EXPERIENCE.
>> JACLYN IS SUCH A LITTLE
PRINCESS THAT YOU HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT JACLYN'S FEELINGS WHEN
PICKING ME FOR REWARD.
>> SHE WILL FLIP.
THEY ARE PILING ON TONIGHT WITH
RIDE, I KNOW THEY ARE.
>> IF JACLYN TELLS JON TO COME
OVER WITH THEM, THEN WE'RE IN
TROUBLE.
THIS WAS THE MOST AMAZING
REWARD, BUT IT'S HARD TO HAVE A
GOOD TIME DAWES BECAUSE WE'RE
NERVOUS THAT JACLYN BEING BACK
AT CAMP WITH THESE THREE GUYS,
SHE COULD EASILY BE SWAYED AND
TOLD THINGS THAT WOULD CHANGE
HER MIND ABOUT HOW SHE FEELS
ABOUT MY MOM, ME, AND NATALIE.
>> OKAY, WE HAVE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
>> ME AND BAYLOR HAVE AN IDOL!
>> WE FOUND IT TWO DAYS AGO.
>> YOU LITTLE ( BLEEP ).
WHY DID YOU KEEP THIS FROM ME?
I'M PROUD OF MY DAUGHTER.
SHE FOUND AN IDOL.
I COULD NOT BELIEVE IT.
I WAS LIKE, WHAT?
TODAY PROVES TO ME THAT SHE'S
PLAYING THIS GAME, AND I'M GOING
TO PAT HER ON THE BUTT THE WHOLE
WAY THROUGH IT.
>> SO FINAL THREE, HOW WOULD YOU
GUYS FEEL ABOUT GOING TOGETHER?
>> I THINK THAT'S OKAY.
>> YOU THINK THAT'S OKAY?
>> I'D BE DOWN.
>> FINAL THREE WITH ME, BAYLOR,
AND MISSY WOULD BE A HANDS
PICKED TEAM.
I WOULD BE A SURE WIN IN MY
HEAD.
ANYTHING COULD HAPPEN BUT I
WOULD BE COMPLETELY COMFORTABLE
GOING TO FINAL THREE WITH THEM.
DO YOU WANT TO SPLIT A BROWNIE?
>> I WANT A FULL ONE.
>> WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> I AM SO DISAPPOINTED IN
MYSELF.
>> WAIT, WHY ARE YOU?
>> BECAUSE, I SHOULDN'T HAVE LET
BAYLOR GET A RISE OUT OF ME.
>> YEAH, SHE DID.
>> SHE DID, AND I JUST-- I
SNAPPED.
IT HAS NOTHING--
>> AND MISSY'S LIKE--
>> IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
GAME.
THAT'S NOT THE WAY I AM IN REAL
LIFE.
>> I DIDN'T THINK MISSY WAS
GOING TO TAKE NATALIE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
THAT'S NOT SMART.
JON JUST WENT TO EXILE, AND I'M
SITTING THERE.
>> YEAH.
>> MAYBE I'M JUST MAD RIGHT NOW.
IT'S JUST SO FUN THEY MISSY
WOULD PICK NATALIE.
LIKE I DON'T KNOW IF THAT WAS
THE SMARTEST MOVE ON MISSY'S
PART, AND MAYBE IT'S JUST ME
BEING HOT HEADED AND MAD BECAUSE
I DIDN'T GET TO GO HORSES BACK
RIDING BUT THAT WAS DUMB.
>> I'D LIKE JACLYN TO ENJOY HER
MEAL TODAY.
>> IT'S ABOUT MAKING HER HAPPY
RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT,
AND WE'LL START THERE WITH
JACLYN?
>> NATURALLY, THE GOAL IS STILL
TO MAKE JACLYN SEE THE LODGE
NICK WHAT HAPPENED TODAY.
MISSY, BAYLOR, AND NATALIE WILL
GO TO THE TOP THREE, AND THEY
WILL TAKE OUT JON AND JACLYN IN
THE PROCESS.
HOPEFULLY, THIS ILLUMINATES THAT
FOR HER AND I'M HOPING TO BE
ABLE TO CAPITALIZE ON THAT
MOVINGED FOR.
>> GIRL, YOU GOT A SHELL FULL OF
RICE.
>> ALL RICE?
>> YUP.
>> THAT?
THAT IS NOT MINE.
>> IT IS.
>> I CAN'T EAT THAT!
ALEC, REED, AND KEITH ARE ALL,
LIKE, BY ME NOW AND BEING SUPER
NICE AND IT'S SO FUNNY.
IT'S LIKE, REALLY, GUYS?
AND I WANT TO SAY, "STOP, STOP
BEING FAKE."
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I'M
INTERESTED TO SEE HOW TONIGHT
PLAYS OUT WITH THE GUYS, AND
WHAT THEY TRY AND PITCH TO ME.
>> BOTH MISSY AND JON ARE
THREATS TO ONE ANOTHER.
AND I'M REALLY CURIOUS TO SEE
WHO'S GOING TO ACT FIRST.
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE MISSY IS
ALREADY ACTING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> SHE JUST ACTED TODAY.
IF YOU DON'T THINK SHE DID.
>> JON IS SO LOYAL, AND HE'S
IT'S ABOUT TRUST, AND STUFF LIKE
THAT.
WHICH IS TRUE.
BUT MISSY IS MORE RUTHLESS THAN
THAT.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU
GUYS GET STEAMS ROLLED BY THAT,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> SO IN THAT CASE I WOULD GO
WITH YOU AND THE GUYS.
S IT NOT THE FIRST TIME JON HAS
CAME BACK FROM EXILE AND I WAS
LIKE HOLD THE PHONE.
WE'RE FLIPPING THE GAME.
AND WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE AGAIN.
IT'S SO FUNNY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY THIS
KEEPS HAPPENING.
>> MAN, THAT COULD BE HUGE.
>> WELCOME BACK.
>> WE GET BACK TO CAMP FROM THE
REWARD THIS MORNING, AND MY FEAR
FOR JACLYN IS THAT REED WAS
GOING TO BEND HER EAR.
SO IT'S IMPORTANT TO KEEP AN EYE
OUT.
>> WE NEED A--
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> HEY, GIRL.
>> I HAVE TO KEEP NURTURING
JACLYN TO MAKE SURE THAT SHE
KNOWS THAT SHE'S STILL GOT ME
BECAUSE I THINK REED WORKS FAST,
AND WHO KNOWS WHAT ALEC SAYS.
>> BAYLOR GETS ON MY NERVES,
MAN.
>> SO ARE YOU LIKE
BROTHER-SISTER, OR WHAT?
OR WOULD YOU TAKE HER ON A DATE?
>> THERE'S, LIKE, NO GIRL I'M
TAKING ON A DATE FROM
"SURVIVOR."
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
UNLESS YOU'RE GOING TO GO ON A
DATE WITH ME.
>> SHUT UP.
>> JACLYN IS A COOL CHICK.
I LIKE JACLYN A LOT.
SO IT WAS A SMART MOVE IN MAKING
HER FEEL AS COMFORTABLE AS SHE
CAN, AND THAT DOESN'T MEAN SHE'S
GOING TO VOTE WITH US, BUT IT'S
NOT GOING TO HURT ANYBODY.
IT'S JUST KIND OF LIKE CREAM
CHEESE-- YOU KNOW, CREAM CHEESE
YOU CAN'T HURT MANY THINGS WITH
PUTTING CREAM CHEESE ON IT.
YOU KNOW I WANTED TO PLAY WITH
YOU AND IT SEEMED LIKE YOU
DIDN'T AT ALL GIVE ME THE TIME
OF DAY, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
>> LOOKING AT ALEC AND JACLYN,
I'M THINKING WHY IS JACLYN
FLIRTING WITH HIM?
JON'S BEEN GONE TWO DAYS, AND
ALEC AND HER BODY LANGUAGE IS
JUST REALLY INAPPROPRIATE.
IF IF I HAD A BOYFRIEND HERE, I
WOULDN'T BE ACTING LIKE THAT
WITH ALEC.
>> I NEED TO GET FAT.
>> I WANT TO HAVE A COMPETITION
WITH YOU AND JON AND DREW.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> IT WOULD BE FUN TO GO OUT.
>> IT MADE ME DEFINITELY FEEL
SUSPICIOUS THAT JACLYN IS
WORKING WITH ALEC MORE CLOSELY
THAN I THOUGHT.
>> MY CONCERN IS DEFINITELY THAT
JACLYN WILL BE SUEDE BY ALAND HE
CAN THE OTHER GUYS, AND IF SHE'S
SWAYED, THEN JON IS SWAYED,
BECAUSE JACLYN AND JON DO
EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
SO JACLYN AND ALEC FLIRTING AND
TALKING ABOUT THE GAME IS JUST
NOT OKAY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
WE'LL NOW BRING IN JON,
RETURNING FROM EXILE ISLAND.
( APPLAUSE )
>> HOW WE DOING, FAMILY?
>> WHAT IS ON YOUR FACE?
SO DIRTY.
>> HOW WE CAN DOING, GUYS?
COME HERE, BABY.
>> YOU'RE FILTHY.
>> I KNOW, I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
REED, HAVE TO TAKE THE NECKLACE
BACK.
NOBODY HELPS ME WITH THE
NECKLACE.
I LIKE IT.
NOBODY WANTS TO LET GO.
>> YOU'RE SO GOOD AT IT.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE AN OVER-SIZED
PADOLE A STAND.
ON MY ANY, YOU'LL ROLL THE BALL
DOWN THE PADDLE AND ATTEMPT TO
LAND IT IN A HOLE.
FIRST PERSON TO GET ONE BALL IN
EACH OF THE SIX HOLES WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE,
GUARANTEED A ONE IN SEVEN SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
BECOME THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
BIG STAKES.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR PADDLES,
MAKE SURE THEY'RE CENTERED ON
THAT STAND.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
SIX BALLS, GOTTA LAND ONE ON
EACH SPOT.
WHICH MEANS YOU WILL HAVE SIX
BALLS ON YOUR PADDLE AT ONE
TIME.
TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
JON RIGHT AWAY LANDS A BALL.
THAT WAS FAST.
REED LANDS ONE RIGHT IN THE
CENTER.
THAT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH TO WORK
AROUND.
REED DROPS.
HE'S BACK TO ZERO.
JON HAS HIS SECOND.
JON'S OFF TO AN EARLY LEAD.
NATALIE HAS ONE.
ALEC STRUGGLING.
KEITH LANDS HIS FIRST BALL.
MISSY HAS ONE.
ALEC HAS ONE.
DOESN'T LAST FOR LONG.
YOU HAVE TO GO FAST ENOUGH TO
BEAT THE OTHER GUY BUT YOU'VE
GOT TO BE IN ENOUGH CONTROL TO
MAKE IT WORK.
JON WITH HIS THIRD, EXTENDING
HIS LEAD.
NATALIE HAS TWO.
KEITH HAS HIS SECOND.
MISSY WORKING ON THAT SECOND.
MISSY HAS TWO.
>> AH!
>> Jeff: KEITH VERY CLOSE TO
HIS THIRD.
OH, JUST FALLS.
KEITH WITH TWO.
JON WORKING ON HIS FOURTH.
NO.
JON DROPS.
KEITH WITH HIS THIRD.
IT'S BETWEEN KEITH AND JON.
EACH WITH THREE.
JON JUST DROPS HIS FOURTH.
EVERYONE ELSE IS FALLING BEHIND.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: KEITH WITH HIS
FOURTH.
JON STILL WORKING ON HIS FOURTH.
KEITH WORKING ON THE FIFTH.
KEITH HAS FIVE.
ONE LEFT FOR KEITH.
JON IS GOING TO HAVE TO HUSTLE
NOW.
KEITH VERY CLOSE ON THAT SIXTH.
OH, KEITH DROPS A BALL.
THE DOOR IS OPEN FOR JON.
JON NOW WITH HIS FOURTH.
KEITH TRYING TO GET THAT SIXTH
AND FINAL BALL.
JON WORKING ON THAT FIFTH.
HE'S GOT TO PICK IT UP.
GOTTA LAND IT HERE.
NO, IT DROPS.
KEITH, DOES HE HAVE THE TOUCH?
HE DOES!
KEITH WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY!
>> YEAH!
GOLLY!
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: KEITH, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
>> JON, REED, BAYLOR.
ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: 29 DAYS IN, GIVEN THE
WAY THINGS HAVE BEEN GOING, I'M
GUESSING THIS FEELS PRETTY GOOD
RIGHT NOW.
>> THIS COMES IN HANDY, YEAH,
GIVEN THE WAY THINGS HAVE BEEN
GOING.
>> Jeff: KEITH CANNOT BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
GUARANTEED A ONE IN SEVEN SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 29
TOUGH DAYS IN NICARAGUA,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT WILL
BECOME THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
IT WON'T BE YOU.
CONGRATS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT APT TRIBAL.
>> GOOD JOB, KEITH.
GOSH.
>> AFTER NOT WINNING IMMUNITY
TODAY, IT MIGHT BE DEAD MAN
WALKING AT THIS POINT.
BUT JON MAY HEAR SOMETHING FROM
JACLYN THAT SPOOKS HIM AND MAYBE
I COULD TAKE OUT MISSY TONIGHT.
SO ESSENTIALLY MY WHOLE PLAN
AGAIN HINGES ON JON AND JACLYN.
>> GOOD JOB, KEITH.
>> SECOND TIME.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> THE BALL MASTER.
>> SO TONIGHT AT TRIBAL, THE
OPTIONS ARE GO WITH REED AND
VOTE OUT MISSY TONIGHT.
AND THEN, YOU KNOW, THERE'S THE
OPTION WITH MISSY AND OUR
ALLIANCE TO VOTE OUT REED
TONIGHT.
>> I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
>> I'M GOING TO BE LOOK, OKAY,
JON, YOU DON'T KNOW THIS
HAPPENED BUT WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
AGAIN AND WE HAVE ANOTHER BIG
DECISION TO MAKE.
I HAVE SO MUCH TO TELL YOU.
LIKE, MY WHOLE PERSPECTIVE
CHANGED AGAIN WHEN YOU WERE
GONE.
WHEN YOU WALKED OUT OF THE
REWARD, MISSY PICKED NATALIE TO
GO WITH THEM.
AND, LIKE, EVERYBODY BEHIND ME
WAS LIKE, "THAT IS A HUGE-- THAT
IS SO TELLING RIGHT THERE WHO'S
GOING TO BE IN THE TOP THREE.
OF.
>> WHEN I GOT BACK AFTER MY
TWO-DAY EXILE, ALL I WANTED TO
DO WAS SPEND TIME WITH HER.
I'VE MISSED HER SO MUCH.
LIKE THE ONLY OTHER THING I DID
WHILE I WAS ON EXILE, I GOT
PARANOID AND I MISSED JACLYN.
>> THE THREE GUYS WANT US TO GO
WITH THEM.
>> THEY'RE ALL LYING.
>> CAN I JUST FINISH BEFORE YOU
FREAK OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THE FIRST THING HAVE
JACLYN THROW ALL THIS PARANOIA
BACK ON ME, IT WAS ALMOST LIKE,
I THOUGHT THIS WAS DONE.
>> REED WANTS US TO BLINDS SIDE
MISSY.
>> I ALREADY KNEW ALL THIS.
I ALREADY KNEW ALL THIS.
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY.
I WON'T TELL YOU ANYMORE.
>> I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
>> HEY!
>> NO!
>> HEY, JACLYN, STOP!
>> WELL, WHAT THE HELL!
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU WHAT
HAPPENED?
>> I KNOW.
GIVE ME A SECOND, I'M SORRY.
HAVE YOU HAD A TWO-DAY EXILE.
>> NO.
>> IT SUCKS.
>> I WANT TO TELL YOU THAT
EVERYBODY IS GOING TO ATTACK YOU
IN, LIKE, 10 MINUTES.
>> I'M GLAD YOU DID.
>> NEXT TIME I WON'T.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> OKAY.
SO JACLYN'S MAD AT ME NOW.
>> THERE'S NO POINT OF US
TALKING RIGHT NOW.
>> I GUESS IN VOICING MY
FRUSTRATION, I THINK JACLYN TOOK
IS AS ME, LIKE, NOT BEING
APPRECIATIVE OF HER GIVING ME
INFORMATION, WHICH THAT'S NOT
THE CASE.
I MEAN, I JUST WANT TO BE WITH
MY GIRLFRIEND.
LET'S TALK FOR A LITTLE BIT.
>> THERE'S NO POINT IN US
TALKING RIGHT NOW.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT?
>> CHILL.
>> NO.
>> LET'S TALK FAIR LITTLE BIT.
>> I DON'T THINK HE REALIZED
WHAT HE WAS DOING WHEN HE
SNAPPED, BUT IF HE THINKS-- YOU
KNOW, THAT HE'S GOT IT-- HE
DIDN'T NEED MY HELP.
IT DIDN'T MATTER WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE TWO DAYS THAT HE WAS
GONE.
HE'LL FIGURE IT OUT FOR HIMSELF.
SO, YOU KNOW, IF HE'S GOT THAT
ATTITUDE, SCREW HIM.
>> HI.
>> I KNOW YOU GUYS ARE-- I
THOUGHT I MIGHT AS WELL JUST
COME OVER AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE
EXACTLY YOU'RE AT WITH
EXPLAINING STUFF TO JON.
YOU HAVE THREE GUYS THAT ARE
REALLY WILLING--
>> NOBODY'S WILLING TO GO TO THE
TOP THREE WITH ME.
DON'T GIVE ME THAT B.S.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO BLINDS
SIDE ME.
>> NOBODY IS TALKING ABOUT
BLINDS SIDING YOU JON.
IT'S ABOUT GETTING ANOTHER STEP
IN THE GAME.
>> IT'S GETTING MISSY OUT TO SET
UP A BLINDS SIDE ON ME.
>> I COULD JUST AS EASILY GO TO
MISSY AND SAWHY NOT WORK WITH ME
AND BLINDS SIDE JON
>> I KNOW.
>> I'M SAYING I LIKE YOU GUYS
BETTER AND I'D RATHER WORK WITH
THE TWO OF YOU.
>> I GET IT.
>> I JUST GOT YELLED AT, TWO.
>> I WOULD RATHER WORK WITH YOU
TWO BECAUSE I LIKE YOU.
IF I HAVE TO GO WORK WITH MISSY
I'LL GO WORK WITH MISSY AT THIS
POINT BUT I DON'T WANT TO.
>> I BELIEVE YOUR WORD MORE THAN
ANYONE ELSE'S, EVEN DESPITE WHAT
HAPPENED AT THE LAST TRIBAL.
LET'S SAY WE VOTE MISSING OUT
THIS TIME.
YOU'RE SAYING TO GO WITH US
THREE AND ALAND HE CAN KEITH.
>> HEY, NAT.
>> I CAN'T-- I CAN'T--
>> THEN--
>> I CAN'T TRUST-- AFTER YOU
VOTED MY NAME ONE TIME, LIKE A
TRIBAL AGO, I CAN'T TRUST A
PITCH FROM YOU BYES.
>> I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> IS IT OKAY IF I'M HERE, GUYS.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, YOU JUST HEARD IT.
>> I WAS KIND OF IN THE MIDDLE
OF DOING THIS PITCH WHEN NATALIE
WALKS UP AND SITS DOWN.
AND JON WINKING AT ME AND GOING,
"THAT'S YI CAN'T TRUST AND YOU
THAT'S WHY I JUST CAN'T WORK
WITH YOU, REED, IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE."
THAT WAS ENCOURAGING BECAUSE IF
HE'S WILLING TO GO OUT ON A LIMB
AND DO A KIND OF WINK THING
BETWEEN US, THEN MAYBE HE'S
CONSIDERING IT A LITTLE MORE
THAN HE WANTS TO LET ON.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I HONESTLY DON'T CARE IF YOU
GUYS WANT TO TALK.
>> NO, WE'RE GOOD.
>> IT'S COOL.
>> I THINK JACLYN GOT A LITTLE
CONFUSED BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
SHE NECESSARILY SAW THE WINK
HAPPEN AND SHE WAS STILL STIEWG
ABOUT I THINK BEING BLOWN UP AT
BY JON, WHICH I'M KIND OF LIKE,
AH, THAT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
>> I TALKED TO JON AND JACLYN.
AND THEY ACTUALLY MIGHT BE
WILLING TO WORK WITH US.
IF WE STAY STRONG, WE MAY HAVE A
SHOT AT I THIS.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE JON IS
STANDING THERE SCRAMBLING WITH
MISSY.
>> I DID FIND THE IDOL.
( LAUGHING )
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU DID?
>> YUP.
I FOUND IT.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I LITERALLY HAVE THE WORST
HEADACHE RIGHT NOW.
TELL ME WHOSE NAME TO WRITE
DOWN.
I DON'T CARE.
AFTER OUR ARGUMENT, THE ONLY
PERSON I WOULD EXPECT JON TO
TALK TO WOULD BE MISSY BECAUSE
HE LOOKS TO HIS MOM FOR ADVICE
IN REAL LIFE, AND I THINK THAT
MISSY HAS TAKEN ON THAT ROLE ON
THE ISLAND.
AND IT MADE ME MAD MAHE TALKED
TO HER FOR, LIKE, A HALF HOUR,
AND DIDN'T COME TALK TO ME AT
ALL.
THAT MADE ME EVEN MORE MAD.
LIKE, YOU'RE NOT FIGHTING WITH
MISSY.
YOU'RE FIGHTING WITH ME.
>> HE JUST FREAKED OUT WHEN I
TRIED TO TELL HIM WHAT HAPPENED
THE LAST TWO DAYS.
>> FREAKED OUT LIKE WHAT.
>> FREAKED OUT ON ME.
SCREW HIM.
HE DOESN'T NEED ME.
I DON'T NEED TO BE HERE.
>> NO, HE DOES NEED YOU.
MY FEARS ARE THAT JON AND JACLYN
ARE NOT AS ATTACHED AT THE HIP
AS THEY SEEMED TO BE WHICH THEY
DO HAVE A LOT OF FRICTION WHEN
IT COMES TO HOW TO PLAY THIS
GAME.
>> OH, GOD.
I'M EVEN MORE ANNOYED RIGHT NOW.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY, I WANT
JON AND JACLYN FINE FOR TONIGHT.
I CAN'T DO ANY MORE SURPRISES AT
TRIBAL.
>> HI.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU
RIGHT NOW.
>> BABE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU
RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M SORRY I SNAPPED.
OKAY.
MY BIG PROBLEM IS WE HAVE A
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT, AND MY
GIRLFRIEND IS NOT ON THE SAME
PAGE AS I AM.
AND SHE REFUSES TO TALK TO ME.
NOT A GOOD TIME TO DO THAT.
>> I FEEL REALLY BAD NOW.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO-- I DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE I WAS, LIKE, EXPLODING ON
HER.
>> JUST NOW?
>> NO, WHEN I FIRST GOT BACK.
>> YOU'VE GOT A LOT TO PROCESS,
BROTHER, A LOT TO PROCESS.
>> JUST TAKE A BREATHER.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
>> WE'VE GOT TO MAKE ANOTHER
WOOD RUN.
>> HI.
>> I'M NOT READY TO TALK YET.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TALK NOW?
>> NO!
STOP!
>> I'M GETTING THE SILENT
TREATMENT RIGHT NOW FROM JACLYN,
AND IT'S THE MOST FRUSTRATING
THING THAT SHE DOES.
THERE'S NO POINT.
TALK IT OUT.
LET'S TALK.
>> NINE DAYS LEFT.
>> THAT CAN BE MY ONLY CHANCE TO
TALK BEFORE TRIBAL, AND JACLYN
IS OVER THERE FLIRTING WITH
ALEC.
SO WHAT DO WE DO?
VOTE FOR REED OR VOTE FOR MISSY.
>> YOU KNOW HOW DISRESPECTED YOU
MADE ME FEEL TODAY.
LIKE, WHY DID YOU YELL AT ME
LIKE YOU DIDN'T WANT TO HEAR
ANYTHING--
>> I WAS OVERWHELMED.
I JUST GOT BACK FROM A TWO-DAY
EXILE.
I MISSED YOU.
LIKE, ALL I WANTED TO DO WAS SIT
DOWN WITH YOU AND RELAX FOR A
MINUTE.
OKAY, YOU KNOW, WHAT?
IT'S NOT EVEN WORTH IT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LISTEN TO
ME, GO BACK BY THE FIRE.
IT'S FINE.
>> I'M LISTENING.
>> YOU'RE ROLLING YOUR EYES.
>> YOU'RE BEING A ( BLEEP ) NOW.
>> I'M PISSED.
>> GOOD!
>> MY WHOLE PLAN HINGES ON JON
AND JACLYN, AND SHE'S FURIOUS.
SHE'S STOMPING AROUND CAMP AND
NOT TALKING TO HIM.
MY LIFE HINGES ON THOSE TWO
TALKING TO EACH OTHER AND
FIGURING OUT WHO THEY WANT TO GO
WITH THIS ALLIANCE OR THAT
ALLIANCE.
>>ALLIANCE.
>> THEN THAT SUCKS FOR YOU.
WELL, HE WON'T TALK TO ME NOW,
SO.
I TRIED.
>> THIS MAY BE A FATAL FIGHT FOR
MY GAME.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JOSH, JEREMY, AND WES VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, JON, AFTER THE CHALLENGE
TODAY WHEN YOU WENT BACK TO
CAMP, DID YOU GET AN UPDATE ON
WHAT HAD HAPPENED AFTER YOU LEFT
AND WAS SENT TO EXILE?
>> YES, I DID.
JACLYN TOOK ME OVER AND GAVE ME
A QUICK UPDATE AND ACTUALLY IT
KIND OF GOT HEATED BETWEEN
JACLYN AND I.
BECAUSE AFTER EXILE, THERE WERE
THINGS THEY NEEDED TO BE CAUGHT
UP ON, SO SHE TOOK THE
OPPORTUNITY TO TAKE ME ASIDE AND
TELL ME THOSE THINGS--
>> AND HE FREAKED OUT ON ME.
>> I GUESS I JUST WASN'T READY
TO HEAR IT ALL.
>> Jeff: SO A FIGHT ERUPTS.
>> BASICALLY.
>> Jeff: HOW BIG A FIGHT,
JACLYN?
>> WELL, HE SNAPPED AT ME PRETTY
BAD AND I FELT LIKE HE DIDN'T
WANT TO HEAR WHAT I WAS SAYING,
HE HAD IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
SO I WAS LIKE, WOW, THAT'S SO
DISRESPECTFUL.
SO THEN I WAS MAD, STARTED
CRYING.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> YEAH.
SO THAT KIND OF LED INTO THE
AFTERNOON.
AND --
>> IS ANYBODY ELSE SEEING THIS
GO ON?
>> EVERYBODY IS SEEING IT GO ON.
>> Jeff: SO THIS IS A PUBLIC
ARGUMENT.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: REED, WHAT DID YOU
SEE?
>> WELL, I FEEL LIKE WHAT WE
KIND OF SAW WAS THE AFTERMATH OF
WHAT HAPPENED.
AND, YOU KNOW, FOR THOSE OF US
WHO ARE STILL TRYING TO PLAY THE
GAME AND TRYING TO STAY IN THE
GAME, IT MADE EVERYTHING JUST
MORE COMPLICATED.
>> Jeff: JON, THIS IS A REALLY
INTERESTING DEVELOPMENT.
WHEN YOU HAVE A LOVED ONE COUPLE
HAVE A REAL-LIFE ARGUMENT IN THE
MIDST OF THE GAME, AND YOU DON'T
KNOW HOW MUCH THEY'VE REALLY
TALKED.
YOU DON'T KNOW IF THEY ARE ON
THE SAME PAGE.
DID YOU SENSE THAT PEOPLE WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU GUYS?
>> YEAH, AND ACTUALLY,
ESPECIALLY REED.
HE DID GET A MINUTE TO TALK TO
BOTH OF US AND KIND OF PITCH A
CASE.
SO --
>> HOLD ON.
SO ONCE AGAIN, YOU AND JACLYN
ARE IN THE MIDDLE.
>> I KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO SAY
THAT.
I KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO SAY
THAT!
>> Jeff: IT'S CRAZY, BUT IT'S
TRUE, RIGHT?
>> YES, WE ARE THE COUPLE THEY
ARE APPROACH GLG YOUR PLEA TO
THEM IS?
>> I SAID AT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE MISSY CHOOSES BAYLOR
AND NATALIE AND CLEARLY WHEN YOU
GET DOWN TO FIVE THE TWO OF YOU
ARE GONE SO WHY DON'T YOU COME
OVER TO ME, ALEC AND KEITH AND
WE'LL FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
>> Jeff: THAT'S NOT GOOD FOR
YOU, MISSY.
>> NO, IT'S NOT GOOD FOR ME AT
ALL.
I THINK IT'S INTERESTING THAT
THEY THINK I'M ON TOP OF SOME
POSITION SAYING YOU GUYS ARE ON
THE BOTTOM.
HOLD UP, LET'S GO BACK TO THIS,
TWO DAYS PRIOR AND THEY TRIED TO
CUT YOUR BOYFRIEND AT THE KNEES,
AND THE ONE SITTING BEHIND YOU
OVER HERE, ALEC, IS NOW FLIRTING
HIS WAY BACK INTO JACLYN.
IT'S THE BIGGEST JOKE!
>> WOW.
>> IT'S SO OBVIOUS.
>> Jeff: LITERALLY FLIRTING?
>> LITERALLY FLIRTING, OVER THE
TOP.
>> JACLYN, WOULD YOU AGREE WITH
THAT, REALLY JAI MEAN, I DON'T
KNOW.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT FOOD, WE
WERE LAUGHING THE OTHER DAY.
MAYBE IT COULD BE PERCEIVED AS
THAT, YES.
>> Jeff: IF I'M LOOKING,
THAT'S A YES.
>> JON, DO YOU THINK ALEC FLIRTS
WITH HER?
>> THERE ARE TIMES I FEEL LIKE
IT'S GETTING A LITTLE-- A LITTLE
WEIRD BUT, LIKE, IT COULD JUST
BE FRIENDLY JIBBER-JABBER.
>> MAYBE I'M TOO NICE AND TOO
FRIENDLY.
>> ALEC HAS BEEN MORE NICE TO ME
THAN HE HAS EVER BEEN.
I WILL SAY THAT.
>> Jeff: WHAT WAS YOUR
RESPONSE, JACLYN, TO REED'S
PITCH?
>> I HONESTLY FELT LIKE PARTS OF
MY HEAD WERE KIND OF BELIEVING
THEM.
I MEAN, I WOULD BE LYING IF I
SAID I WASN'T HURT BY THE FACT
THAT MISSY CHOSE NATALIE TO GO.
BUT THEN AT THE SAME TIME, I
COME BACK TO CAMP, AND ALL THE
GRIEZ LIKE, WELL, THAT'S THE
FINAL THREE AND IT'S VERY
TELLING, SO THERE'S A LOT OF
PARANOIA CREATED IN MY HEAD.
AND IT'S NOT BEEN THE EASIEST.
AND, JEFF, IT'S NOT GREAT FOR
THE REST OF US BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW, THEY CAN DO WHAT THEY
WANT.
THEY'RE A LITTLE BIT LUCK THEY
THEY GET TO CHOOSE WHICH
ALLIANCE THEY WANT TO BE WITH.
>> Jeff: SO, MISSY, WHAT'S THE
LEVEL OF CONCERN THAT THAT ONE
DECISION COULD PUT YOU OUT OF
THIS GAME?
>> THERE'S A LEVEL OF CONCERN
BECAUSE I KNEW GOING BACK THAT
SHE WAS GOING TO BE APPROACHED.
I MEAN, I KNEW IT, SO, YEAH,
THAT DECISION OF CHOOSING
NATALIE COULD COST ME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
KEITH, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU HAVE TO GO BECAUSE YOU'RE
A BIG RABBLE-ROUSER.
AND BY THE WAY, MY CHILD'S NOT A
BRAT.
>> THIS THE WILL LIKELY BE THE
ONLY TIME I EVER WRITE YOUR NAME
DOWN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, REED.
MISSY.
REED.
THAT'S TWO VOTES REED.
THAT'S THREE VOTES REED, ONE
VOTE MISSY.
REED.
FOUR VOTES REED.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, REED.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
REED, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> OUCH, JEFF.
>> Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> THANKS.
>> Jeff: AND THAT'S WHY "BLOOD
VERSUS WATER" IS SO DIFFICULT.
WHEN YOU PLAY WITH A LOVED ONE,
YOU BRING YOUR PERSONAL LIFE
INTO AN ALREADY-COMPLICATED
GAME, AND WITH FOUR LOVED ONES
LEFT, THIS WON'T BE THE LAST
TIME YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH IT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> THIS EXPERIENCE HAS BEEN THE
MOST AMAZING/TERRIFYING
EXPERIENCE I THINK I'VE EVER HAD
IN MY LIFE.
THIS HAS BROUGHT JOSH AND I EVEN
CLOSER WITH BOTH BEING SUCH
SUPER NERDS ABOUT THIS SHOW BUT
BEING ABLE TO SHARE THIS
TOGETHER HAS BEEN SO INCREDIBLE.
SO PROBST, SNUFFED MY TORCH
TONIGHT, WHICH IN AN ODD WAY IS
A DREAM COME TRUE, TOO.
>> I KNOW.
>> THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME WE'VE
ALL BEEN ON THE SAME PAGE ABOUT
A VOTE, THOUGH, GOOD LORD.
>> I'M REALLY SORRY.
>> ME, TOO.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TOWRND MINE
YOU.
>> IT'S FINE.
>> I REALLY APPRECIATE YOUR
OPINION, AND I LOVE YOU.
>> OKAY.
JON AND I, WE KIND OF RESOLVED
EVERYTHING AT TRIBAL, WHICH WAS
PRETTY INTERESTING.
WE'RE FINE.
HE SAID SORRY, AND I SAID SORRY.
SO I'M HAPPY IT'S OVER BECAUSE
TODAY WAS SERIOUSLY EMOTIONALLY
DRAINING.
IT'S BEEN A LONG DIE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> TRIBAL GOT KIND OF HEATED
TONIGHT.
EVERYONE THINKS I'M A BIG FLIRT,
BUT THAT IS A SICK JOKE.
IF I WANTED TO FLIRT WITH ANY OF
THESE GIRLS HERE, I WOULD, BUT I
WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
STILL, SEEING ALL THESE OTHER
LOVED ONES TOGETHER IS TOUGH.
IT REALLY IS TOUGH.
AND IT REALLY DIDN'T HIT ME
UNTIL TONIGHT, BUT I'VE GOT
LITERALLY NO ONE TO COME AND
TALK TO AFTER TRIBAL.
AND IT JUST SUCKS.
SO I DON'T HAVE MUCH TO HOLD ON
TO, BUT I'M STILL HOLDING ON.
>> BREAKFAST!
>> YEAH!
SEEING YOU GUYS CAN GO AND
RELATE WITH MISSY AND BAYLOR AND
IT'S JUST LIKE-- I'M JUST LIKE
HERE BY MYSELF.
>> I HONESTLY DO NOT BELIEVE
THAT KEITH OR ALEC HAVE ANY PLAY
LEFT IN THE GAME.
>> I TOLD YOU I WAS GOING TO BE
STRAIGHTED FOR, RIGHT.
AND I'M GOING TO BE.
I HONESTLY DO NOT SEE FINDING A
CRACK AND SPLITTING US UP, AND
LOOKING FROM YOUR PERSPECTIVE,
IT PROBABLY SOUND LIKE I'M
TALKING "SURVIVOR" SUICIDE, BUT
I-- I TRUST THEM.
I REALLY DO.
>> IT DOES ACTUALLY SEEM LIKE I
FOUND PEOPLE WHO ARE TRUSTWORTHY
AND UNLESS I AM READING
EVERYTHING WRONG, WHICH I
HAVEN'T YET, I'M STILL
CONTROLLING AND STEERING THE
DIRECTION OF THE GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO STAND ON A SMALL BLOCK,
WHILE STABILIZING A BALL AGAINST
AN OVER-HANGING PIECE OF WOOD.
IF AT REQUEST POINT, YOU LOSE
JUR CONCENTRATION ON YOUR
BALANCE, THE BALL WILL DROP, AND
EUROPE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER WILL HAVE
DELIVERED TO CAMP A KING-SIZED
CANOPY BED.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: YOU WILL ENJOY A NICE
MEAL IN THAT BED-- SPAGHETTI.
CHICKEN PARMESAN.
GARLIC BREAD.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: WINE, AND DESSERT.
>> IT'S OVER.
>> Jeff: IT'S YOUR BEST SHOT
TO GET A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP ON A
FULL BELLY ON DAY 30 HEADING
INTO THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
AND AS ALWAYS, THE WINNER WILL
DECIDE WHO GOES TO EXILE ISLAND.
BIG STAKES.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I'M WINNING THIS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY
TAKE YOUR POSITIONS.
PLACE YOUR BALL, STABILIZE IT
AGAINST THE WOOD.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE STABLE.
GOTTA KEEP ONE FOOT ONLY ON THAT
BLOCK.
EVERYBODY LOOKS GOOD.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
ANOTHER TEST.
THIS ONE REQUIRES CONCENTRATION
AND BALANCE.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, ALEC DROPS
QUICKLY.
HE'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT REWARD.
30 DAYS OF FRUSTRATION SETTING
IN.
WE'RE DOWN TO SIX NOW.
YOU CANNOT LET YOUR
CONCENTRATION LAPSE.
ALL IT TAKES IS JUST A LITTLE
MOVEMENT.
THE BALL THE SLIDE OUT, AND
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
JACLYN WITH A NICE RECOVERY.
THIS WILL BE A BIG WIN, FOOD AND
SLEEP, TWO THINGS YOU TAKE FOR
GRANTED BACK HOME.
NOT OUT HERE.
OUT HERE, YOU HAVE TO EARN IT.
EVERYBODY FEELING IT NOW.
THIS IS NOT EASY.
JON'S BALL WEDGING A LITTLE TO
THE SIDE.
FATIGUE STARTING TO SET IN ON
THE ARMS.
YOU'RE FEELING IT IN ALL PART OF
YOUR BODY-- YOUR FEET, YOUR
BACK.
KEITH WITH SOME MOVEMENT.
MISSY'S BALL'S STARTING TO SLIDE
UP A BIT.
JON'S BALL MOVING SOME MORE.
KEEP CONCENTRATING.
KEEP PRESSURE AGAINST THAT BALL,
NOT TOO MUCH, THOUGH.
MISSY DROPS OUT.
MISSY, SECOND PERSON OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
GOING TO TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH, JOINING ALEC.
A LITTLE BIT OF MOVEMENT FROM
BAYLOR.
KEITH DROPS OUT.
NO SHOT AT REWARD FOR KEITH.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
JOB FIGHTING.
THAT BALL HAS BEEN MOVING THE
ENTIRE CHALLENGE, BUT HE'S STILL
UP THERE.
NOT ONLY ARE YOU PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
YOU'RE TRYING TO BUILD YOUR CASE
IF YOU GET TO FINAL TRIBAL TO
SHOW THAT YOU WON SOMETHING.
>> GOD.
YEAH, I DON'T GOT THAT GOING FOR
ME.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR DROPS OUT.
WE'RE DOWN TO THREE.
JON'S BALL IS JUST HANGING ON
THE SIDE OF THE BOARD BUT IT'S
STILL THERE.
>> JON'S IN TROUBLE HERE IT
LOOKS LIKE.
>> Jeff: JON'S BALL MOVING A
LITTLE MORE.
HE'S TRYING TO GET IT BACK.
>> JON, JON, JON, JON, JON.
>> Jeff: JON SUCCESSFULLY GOT
HIS BALL BACK CENTERED, A GREAT
RECOVERY.
PUTS HIM RIGHT BACK IN THIS.
A LITTLE MOVEMENT FROM JACLYN'S
BALL DOWN ON THE END.
JON STRUGGLING AGAIN TO KEEP
THAT BALL BALANCED.
SLOWLY TRYING TO RECOVER YET
AGAIN.
JON CAN'T HANG ON ANY LONGER.
BIG EFFORT, CAME UP SHORT, AND
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS NATALIE AND JACLYN, FOR
REWARD.
KEEP DIGGING.
"SURVIVOR" PUSHES YOU TO GO PAST
THAT PLACE OF COMFORT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO RIGHT
NOW.
JACLYN WITH ANOTHER NICE
RECOVERY.
NATALIE STRUGGLING NOW.
JACLYN DROPS OUT.
NATALIE WINS REWARD.
( APPLAUSE )
>> GOOD JOB, NAT.
>> GOOD JOB, GIRL.
>> GOOD JOB, NATALIE.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, COME ON
OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, NAT.
>> GOOD JOB.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BIG REWARD
FOR NATALIE.
FIRST THING YOU HAVE TO DECIDE,
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SEND TO
EXILE ISLAND.
>> IT WILL BE ALEC.
>> Jeff: NO HESITATION.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S WHATEVER.
I FIGURED IT WAS COMING.
IT'S NOT REALLY A SURPRISE.
>> Jeff: ALEC, HERE'S A MAP TO
EXILE.
YOU WILL RETURN IN TIME FOR THE
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> GOOD LUCK, ALEC.
>> HANG IN THERE.
>> FIND SOME CRABS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NATALIE,
BIG REWARD.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: KING-SIZED BED, FOOD
DELIVERED.
INVITE ONE PERSON TO JOIN YOU.
>> I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GO WITH
JACLYN.
SHE TALKS ABOUT SPAGHETTI MORE
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
>> I LOVE YOU!
>> Jeff: IT IS A KING-SIZED
BED.
YOU THINK YOU COULD FIT ANOTHER?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, INVITE ONE
MORE.
>> JON.
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> I WAS GOING TO SAY MAYBE JON
AND JACLYN ALONE, BUT NO GETTING
FREAKY TONIGHT, GUYS.
>> Jeff: MISSY.
>> YOU'RE ALREADY GETTING READY
TO LEAVE.
HOW DOES THIS FEEL, MISSY.
YOU'VE BEEN IN THIS SITUATION ON
THE OTHER SIDE WHEN YOU CHOSE
AND SOMEBODY WAS DISAPPOINTED.
>> YEAH, AND IT'S GOING TO BE AT
CAMP, SO THAT'S NOT FUN.
>> UH-OH.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE RUBBED RIGHT
IN OUR FACES, SO THAT'S THE
DIFFERENCE.
>> YUP.
>> I'M USED TO IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NATALIE,
JACLYN, JON, NICE REWARD.
BED WILL BE DELIVERED.
HAVE A GOOD MEAL.
KEITH, MISSY, BAYLOR, GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> I'VE BEEN WANTED TO GET JON
OUT SO PICKING JACKIE AND JON
FOR REWARD SHOWS I'M SUCH A
LOYAL PERSON AND THEY WILL TRUST
ME MORE SO WHEN I TAKE MY
REVENGE, HE WILL NEVER SEE IT
COMING.
>> OH, MY GOD, IT'S BIG.
>> IT'S SO PRETTY.
>> WE GOT BACK FROM THE REWARD,
AND THE BED WAS SET UP.
PART OF YOU IS SO HAPPY, LIKE
OH, MY GOSH, SOMETHING
COMFORTABLE TO LAY ON.
WHAT?
>> THIS WOULD LOOK GOOD IN THE
GUEST BEDROOM.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT THEN YOU LOOK OVER AT THE
OTHER PEOPLE, AND YOU REALIZE,
OH, WE'RE GOING TO BE ENJOYING
THAT WHILE THEY'RE STARING AT
US.
>> THEY'RE TALKING.
>> GO GRAB SOME WATER.
>>IARY GOING TO GO GET WATER?
>> I FEEL LIKE SOMETHING WEIRD
IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> MISSY, BAYLOR, AND KEITH KIND
OF JUST LEFT AND WALKED OFF, AND
I WAS LIKE WHAT IS GOING ON?
BUT JON HAS HAD A REALLY STRONG
BOND WITH MISSY FROM THE
BEGINNING, SO HOPEFULLY WE CAN
KEEP GOING WITH THAT AND NOTHING
CRAZY WILL HAPPEN.
>> I JUST FEEL SO BAD.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE MISSY'S
PISSED.
>> IT WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
THEY'LL GET OVER IT, BUT RIGHT
NOW IT'S BITTER BECAUSE THEY
SEE--
>> GUYS, YOU ARE BEING SO
PARANOID.
YOU GUYS ARE THE WORST.
EVERYBODY NEEDS TO JUST HANG OUT
WITH ME AND EVERYBODY WILL BE
FINE.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
AS WE'RE APPROACHING THE END OF
THIS GAME, THERE ARE ALWAYS
CHANCES FOR WEIRD THINGS TO
HAPPEN.
BUT I'VE GROWN TO TRUST MISSY A
LOT.
AND THE MORE I GET TO KNOW
NATALIE, THE MORE REASSURED I AM
OF THE STRENGTH OF OUR ALLIANCE.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS, CHEERS TO
DAY 30, AND THEN WE CAN START.
>> CHEERS.
>> REWARD AT THIS POINT IN THE
GAME IS WAY MORE THAN JUST
GETTING TO SLEEP IN A BED AND
ENJOYING PASTA AND CHICKEN PARM.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS WHAT I HAVE BEEN
DREAMING ABOUT FOR 30 DAYS.
>> EVERYBODY IS SO COMFORTABLE
NOW.
THEY PROBABLY WANT TO GET RID OF
KEITH BECAUSE KEITH'S CONNECTION
WITH THE JURY IS SCARY.
BUT I WANT TO BLINDED SIDE JON.
I'M GETTING BACK AT JON FOR
JEREMY.
I DON'T TRUST JON IN THE LONG
RUN.
I WANT TO MOVEED FOR WITH A NEW
PLAN WITHOUT JON IN IT YOU CAN
HAVE MY WINE.
>> THANKS!
>> CALL ME A WINE SNOB, BUT I
LIKE WINE BECAUSE IT'S A MEMORY
OF MY DAD TEACH MEEG HOW TO
DRINK WINE PROPERLY.
THERE WERE SO MANY LAYERS OF
COMPLEXITY TO WINE.
THAT THE FURTHER YOU GET INTO
IT, THE MORE YOU REALIZE OH, MY
GOSH.
I HAVEN'T EVEN TOUCHED THE
SURFACE OF IT.
AND IT'S SUCH A CONVERSATION
PIECE.
I WANT TO GET MY REP PORUP FOR
BEING A SOMELLIER.
I WILL PROBABLY END UP WORKING
IN ONE OF THE NICE
ESTRESTAURANTS IN LAS VEGAS.
IT WILL BE, LIKE, A YEAR IN LAS
VEGAS AND THEN WE FINISH LIVING
A YEAR IN ITALY.
>> OH, MY GOD, AMAZING.
JON IS ALWAYS BRINGING UP ANY
EXCUSE TO TALK ABOUT WINE AND
HOW HE WANTS TO-- I DON'T KNOW,
BE SOME KIND OF WINE SPECIALIST
IN THE FUTURE AND MOVE TO VEGAS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT, BUT HE IS
ALWAYS TRYING TO PRETEND HE
KNOWS EVERYTHING AND THE
ARROGANCE OR ENTITLEMENT JON
HAS.
HONESTLY, EVERY TIME HE TALKS
ABOUT WINE I JUST WANT TO BE
LIKE SHUT UP.
IT WAS TORTURE, BASICALLY.
ARE WE GOING TO TALK STRATEGY AT
ALL.
>> WHAT STRATEGY DO WE NEED TO
TALK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE I CAN TRUST
100% THAT THE PLAN IS WHAT WE
SAY IT IS BECAUSE WE FEEL LIKE
WE CAN TRUST YOU VERY WELL.
HOW ABOUT THIS.
BECAUSE OF HOW COMFORTABLE WE
ARE WITH YOU, I DID FIND THE
IDOL.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> THAT'S SO CRAZY.
>> YOU'VE HAD SO MUCH LUCK ON
EXILE.
JON SHOULD NOT TRUST ME BUT I'M
HAPPY THAT HE DOES.
THE FACT THAT HE TOLD ME THAT HE
FOUND AN IDOL ON EXILE IS
AMAZING BECAUSE I'VE BECOME LIKE
THE BEST FRIEND NOW FOR HIM.
GETTING JON OUT NOW IS REALLY
IMPORTANT.
I JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
DO ALL THIS, AND IF I COULD FULL
OFF, THAT WOULD BE AMAZING.
>> YOU WERE MOVING A LOT.
>> I KNOW, SORRY.
I WAS STUCK IN THE MIDDLE.
IT FREAKED ME OUT.
I WAS JUST LISTENING TO HIM TALK
AND TALK AND TALK.
HE FEELS SO COMFORTABLE AFTER
LAST NIGHT.
HE'S ALREADY BANKING ON WHAT
HE'S GOING TO DO WITH THE
MILLION DOLLARS.
HE'S LIKE I CAN'T WAIT TO DO
THIS AND THIS AND THIS.
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT MONEY.
>> EVERYTHING.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE GAME FOR
THEM.
IT'S JUST ABOUT THEM AND THEIR
PERFECT LIFE THEY WANT AS A
COUPLE.
JON IS VERY CONFIDENT.
HE THINKS THAT IT'S GOING TO BE
A REALLY EASY CAKEWALK TO THE
FINAL THREE BECAUSE HE HAS MISSY
AROUND HIS FINGER.
HE THINKS BAYLOR IS NOT GOING TO
DO ANYTHING TO MESS UP HIS MOM'S
PLAN.
HE HAS HIS GIRLFRIEND WRAPPED
AROUND HIS FINGER AND HE THINKS
I'M GOING TO DO WHATEVER HE
WANTS.
>> HE'S SUCH A PUNK.
>> I JUST WANT HIM OUT.
>> YEAH.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S OBNOXIOUS,
JON'S PLAYED A REALLY GOOD GAME.
THE MORE AND MORE I'M THINKING
OF THE JURY, WHY RISK EVEN GOING
TO FINAL THREE WITH SOMEBODY
LIKE JON.
IF HE WINS, I WILL LITERALLY
KILL MYSELF.
I SAY WE VOTE OUT JON.
BUT DON'T TELL MISSY BECAUSE
THESE NOT GOING TO VOTE JON OFF.
YOUR MOM IS KIND OF BLINDED BY
JON.
>> NOT ONLY THAT, MY NOM IS
BLINDED BY TRYING TO HELP HIM.
>> ME AND NATALIE ARE KIND OF
"SURVIVOR"" SISTER AT THIS POINT
AND DECIDED TO GET RID OF JON.
UNFORTUNATELY, MY MOM, MY
CLOSEST ALLIANCE HERE, IS
ALIGNED WITH HIM.
>> HOW WAS IT?
SO GOOD?
>> IT WAS GOOD.
IT'S WEIRD, OBVIOUSLY, BECAUSE
WE'RE, LIKE SITTING OVER THERE
AND THE WHOLE TIME WE'RE LIKE,
THIS SUCTION, WE CAN'T JUST
SHARE THIS WITH EVERYBODY.
>> JON JUST REMIND ME TOO MUCH
OF PAST MEN IN MY MOM'S LIFE
WHERE SHE GETS BLINDS SIDED,
HEARTBROKEN AND HURT AND I DON'T
WANT HIM TO SCREW HER OVER.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ME FEEL BAD
VOTING HIM OUT.
>> ME, YOU, KEITH, AND ALEC.
I KNOW THEY WILL VOTE HIM
BECAUSE THEY DON'T LIKE JON.
JUST HOPEFULLY HE DOESN'T WIN
IMMUNITY.
>> THEY SLEEP ALL NIGHT AND THEY
SLEEP ALL DAY.
I'M BEHIND THE 8 BALL RIGHT NOW,
AND IT PISSES ME OFF THAT JON'S
JUST COASTING.
I DON'T HAVE NO STROKE OUT HERE.
I'M NOT THE CAPTAIN OUT THERE.
THAT FIVE-SOME THEY'VE GOT IS
TIGHT.
I'M ON THE OUTSIDE LOOKING IN.
I FEEL LIKE SOMEBODY IS GOING TO
BOLT BEFORE LONG AND HOPEFULLY
THEY'LL BOLT MY WAY.
>> TODAY, I GOT A VERY WEIRD
VIBE FROM CAMP.
AND IT WORRIED ME BECAUSE WE'RE
SO CLOSE TO THE END.
A WEIRD VIBE CAN MEAN VERY BAD
THINGS.
>> I FEEL LIKE SOMETHING'S GOING
ON BACK THERE.
DO YOU REALLY TRUST NATALIE?
>> YEAH.
>> MAYBE I'M JUST BEING
PARANOID.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T TRUST ANYBODY OUT HERE,
HONESTLY.
BUT IF-- BUT YOU HAVE A
CONNECTION WITH THEM.
I DON'T.
>> I'M WORRIED THAT KEITH IS
TRYING TO SWAY MISSY, BAYLOR,
AND NATALIE TO PROBABLY VOTE OUT
JON.
IT JUST MAKES ME SO NERVOUS THAT
JON THINKS HE GOT IT IN THE BAG,
AND THAT'S HOW WE ARE IN REAL
LIFE, TOO.
LIKE, HE GETS SUPER AMPED UP FOR
STUFF AND REALLY POSITIVE AND,
"I GOT IT."
AND THEN IT DOESN'T HAPPEN AND
HE'S SUPER DISAPPOINTED.
AND I'M WORRIED IF HE'S NOT
CAREFUL, THAT COULD HAPPEN TO
HIM AGAIN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WE'LL NOW BRING IN ALEC,
RETURNING FROM EXILE ISLAND.
>> YAY!
( APPLAUSE )
>> ALEC!
>> HI, GUYS.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, WHAT'S THE
EMOTIONAL STATE OF THIS GROUP?
YOU HAVE BEEN OUT HERE NOW 32
DAYS.
>> YEAH, THE EMOTIONAL STATE IS
DEFINITELY FATIGUE, BUT HAVING
LOVED ONES THAT ARE FATIGUED
REALLY CAN AFFECT YOUR OWN GAME.
>> Jeff: MISSY, WHAT'S GOING
ON.
YOU'RE HOLDING BACK THE TEARS.
>> I'M FINE.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S BRINGING ON
THE TEARS?
CAN YOU PINPOINT IT?
>> IT'S-- IT'S JUST PHYSICAL.
IT IS-- I MEAN, I'M SO DEPLETED.
IT'S NOT EVEN FOOD FOR ME.
IT'S SLEEP.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, WHAT'S IT
LIKE TO SEE YOUR MOM, WHO FOR
MOST OF YOUR LIFE HAS PROBABLY
BEEN THE SOURCE OF STRENGTH, AND
NOW YOU'RE GETTING TO SEE HER
SHOW A VULNERABLE SIDE THAT MOMS
DON'T OFTEN SHOW TO THEIR KIDS?
>> I JUST WISH I COULD GIVE HER
SOME OF MY ENERGY AND STRENGTH
BECAUSE I KNOW YOU COULD MAKE IT
SEVEN MORE DAYS, BUT I CAN'T.
SO I JUST GOTTA BE THERE FOR HER
AS MUCH AS I CAN AS A DAUGHTER.
>> Jeff: IT'S CLEAR, ALL OF
YOU ARE STRUGGLING ON SOME LEVEL
EMOTIONALLY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET IT TOGETHER
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE IT'S TIME TO
GET TO ANOTHER IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, KEITH, I'M
GOING TO TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO PULL ON A ROPE
BALANCING A WOBBLY TABLE.
YOU'LL RACE OUT TO COLLECT A
SERIES OF WOODEN BLOCKS,
BRINGING THEM BACK ONE AT A TIME
AND PLACING THEM ON THE TABLE.
IF YOUR TABLE WOBBLES AND BLOCKS
FALL, YOU'LL HAVE TO RACE TO
RESET THEM BEFORE HEADING BOOK
OUT.
THE FIRST PERSON TO PLACE ALL 10
OF THEIR BLOCKS, WINS IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A ONE IN SIX SHOT AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
BECOME THE FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
WE'RE GOING TO DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO, FOR
IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THAT FIRST ONE IS AN EASY ONE.
YOU NODE TO GET A FEEL FOR HOW
THE TABLE WORKS.
YOU HAVE TO FIND OUT HOW FAST I
CAN ANY WITHOUT TOO FAST?
ALEC QUICKLY LEARNING WHAT TOO
FAST MEANS.
THAT'S ALL PART OF LEARNING THIS
CHALLENGE.
KEITH MOVING QUICKLY.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR THAT SPOT
BETWEEN BRAZEN AND RECKLESS.
JUST KEEP TRYING TO LEARN WHERE
IS THAT SWEET SPOT FOR ME?
BECAUSE YOU WANT TO GO AS A
MATTER OF FACT YOU CAN WHILE
MAINTAINING THE LEVEL.
KEITH WITH ANOTHER.
>> HOW IS HE GETTING IT?
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY LOOKING
VERY STEADY.
KEITH STILL IN THE LEAD.
JON COMING BACK WITH ANOTHER.
MOVING SLOW AND STEADY.
ALEC, BAYLOR, JON, MISSY, JACLYN
WITH THREE.
KEITH WITH FOUR.
KEITH IS FLYING THROUGH THIS
CHALLENGE.
BAYLOR DROPS, GOTTA GO BACK AND
STACK THEM.
ALEC DROPS HIS, GOTTA GO BACK.
KEITH DROPS HIS, HE'S GOT TO GO
BACK.
THAT'S HOW QUICKLY THIS
CHALLENGE CAN CHANGE.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR FOR
EVERYBODY ELSE.
EVERY TIME YOU DUMP YOUR TABLE,
IT COSTS YOU A LOT OF TIME.
BUT THE ONLY WAY TO WIN IS TO BE
FASTER THAN EVERYBODY ELSE.
JACLYN WITH HER SIXTH.
JON PLACES HIS SIXTH.
BEEN MOVING SLOW AND STEAD
THEENTIRE CHALLENGE.
THERE'S KEITH FINALLY BACK WITH
NUMBER SIX.
NATALIE WITH HER SIXTH.
JO JON AND JACLYN WITH SEVEN.
HERE IS BAYLOR WITH NUMBER 6.
SHE NEEDS TO PICK IT UP.
KEITH CAN SEVEN.
IT'S JON, JACLYN, AND KEITH IN
THE LEAD.
MISSY SLOWING DOWN.
ALEC DUMPS AGAIN.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: JACLYN DROPS.
SHE'S FALLING OUT OF IT.
JON AND KEITH IN THE LEAD.
COMING BACK WITH THEIR EIGHTH.
BIG IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
NATALIE IS STILL IN IT, COMING
BACK HER EIGHTH.
RIGHT NOW IT IS KEITH AND JON IN
THE LEAD.
KEITH DROPS HIS!
HE'S GOT TO COME BACK.
JON NOW IN THE LEAD HEADING BACK
WITH HIS NINTH.
NATALIE HAS EIGHT.
JON WOULD LOVE TO WIN IMMUNITY
RIGHT NOW ON DAY 32 AND
GUARANTEE HIMSELF A SPOT IN THE
FINAL SIX, AND SHE IS VERY
CLOSE.
KEITH HAS GOT TO HUSTLE.
JON PLACES HIS NINTH.
KEITH HEADING BACK NOW LOOKING
FOR HIS NINTH.
JON HEADING BACK VERY SLOWLY.
WILL IT PAY OFF?
HERE COMES KEITH WITH NUMBER
NINE.
HE'S TRYING TO PICK UP THE PACE.
JON COMING BACK WITH HIS TENTH,
BUT HE'S MOVING VERY SLOWLY.
OPENING THE DOOR FOR KEITH TO
CATCH UP.
KEITH HEADING OUT FOR HIS TENTH.
IT IS JON AND KEITH FOR
IMMUNITY.
KEITH HAS TO HUSTLE.
KEITH COMING BACK WITH HIS TENTH
BLOCK, BUT HE DROPS EVERYTHING,
OPENS THE DOOR FOR JON TO WIN
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY RIGHT HERE.
ALL THEE HAS TO DO IS KEEP THAT
TABLE STEADY.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
JON WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY!
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> GOOD JOB!
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY I'M CRYING
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: JON, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: BIG WIN ON DAY 32.
JON CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THE
GAME TONIGHT.
THAT MEANS YOU ARE GUARANTEED
ONE IN SIX SHOT AT WINNING THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 32
OBVIOUSLY VERY TOUGH DAYS,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT,
WILL BECOME THE FIFTH MEMBER OF
OUR JURY, AND WILL HAVE A BIG
HAND IN DECIDING WHO WINS THIS
GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL,
CONGRATS.
>> I LITERALLY THOUGHT WE COULD
GET OUT JON TONIGHT AND WE WON
IMMUNITY SO WE HAVE TO COME UP
WITH A PLAN "B" AND FAST.
I'M FEELING OH, MY GOD, NOW WHAT
DO I DO?
>> HOME, SWEET HOME.
>> GOOD JOB, JON!
>> THANKS!
WINNING THIS IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
WAS ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
ESPECIALLY WHEN GOING INTO IT, I
DID HAVE A FEW WORRIES ABOUT MY
ALLIANCE.
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT I WAS JUST
BEING A LITTLE PARANOID, BUT
IT'S A GREAT FEELING GOING INTO
TRIBAL HAVING THE NECKLACE.
I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
ANYTHING GOING ON TONIGHT.
JUST FOCUS ON WHAT WE NEED TO
DO.
JUST IN CASE ONE OF THEM SOMEHOW
HAS AN IDOL, WE HAVE THE
NUMBERS.
WE SHOULD JUST SPLIT THE VOTE
JUST TO BE SAFE.
THREE ON KEITH, AND AS LONG AS
HE DOESN'T PLAY AN IDOL, HE'S
GOING HOME.
>> EXACTLY.
>> TRIBAL TONIGHT, THE PLAN IS
TO GET KEITH OUT.
HE'S AN INCREDIBLE THREAT AND
NALL IMMUNITY CHALLENGES.
HE'S BEEN RIGHT IN THE FIGHT IN
EVERY SINGLE ONE.
HE'S WON TWO OF THEM.
SO HE NEEDS TO GO.
>> JON WANTS TO SPLIT THE VOTES,
AND THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
JON IS MY GUY.
HE'S GOT MY BACK.
SO OUR FAB FIVE IS STRONG, AND
WE'RE SENDING KEITH HOME.
>> ME, YOU, AND JON ON KEITH,
AND MISSY AND BAYLOR ON ALEC.
>> EITHER WAY, I GUESS IT'S GOOD
TO SCARE ALEC, TOO, AND NOT MAKE
HIM FEEL COMFORTABLE.
>> LET'S SPLIT.
WE MIGHT AS WELL.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
JON WINDS IMMUNITY, AND I WAS
JUST SO MAD.
I FELT LIKE EVERYTHING I WAS
DOING FOR THE LAST COUPLE OF
DAYS WAS JUST DOWN THE CRANE,
AND IT MAKES ME REALLY DEPRESSED
AT THIS POINT.
EVERYTHING DITO GET HIM OUT, AND
I CAN'T KICK HIM OUT.
I GAVE HIM THE REWARD BECAUSE I
WANTED TO BLINDS SIDE HIM.
>> TRUST ME, I WAS ON BOARD FOR
TODAY.
>> KEITH, STUPID ASS.
>> I KNOW, HE FREAKED OUT.
>> I NEED HIMED TO WIN THAT.
>> IT COMPLETELY SUCKS THAT JON
WON IMMUNITY TODAY.
NATALIE AND I WERE BANKING ON
HIM NOT WINNING AND NOW IT'S
BACK TO THE DRAWING BOARD AND
IT'S FRUSTRATING BECAUSE THERE'S
NOT MUCH TIME LEFT.
>> EVERYBODY I WAS CLOSE WITH IN
THE GAME IS GONE.
BESIDES YOU.
BUT I'M JUST SAYING, YOU'RE
GOING TO VOTE ME OUT, TOO.
DEFINITELY SEEMS LIKE A TOSS-UP
BETWEEN KEITH AND MYSELF.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO GIVE UP.
I MEAN, MY BACK'S AGAINST THE
WAW, AND I JUST GOTTA START
SWINGING.
SO WHATEVER I HAVE TO DO,
WHOEVER I HAVE TO LIE TO, FLIRT
WITH, WHATEVER, I'M WILLING TO
DO IT AT THIS POINT.
I'M NOT, LIKE, AN EMOTIONAL
DUDE.
NORMALLY I'M, LIKE, SUPER TOUGH,
AND I JUST SAY ( BLEEP ) AND DO
MY OWN THING AND I'LL BE FINE.
I JUST KIND OF LOST THAT.
WHAT?
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
>> I'M JUST GETTING WISDOM FROM
ALEC, AND I LIKE IT.
>> I'M NOT GIVING YOU WISDOM.
IT'S NOT WISDOM.
>> I'M GETTING TRUE FEELINGS
FROM ALEC.
THAT'S-- THAT'S NEW.
>> YEAH.
I NORMALLY DON'T SHARE MY
FEELINGS AND EMOTIONS.
BUT THIS GAME HAS REALLY DONE
SOMETHING TO ME.
>> ALEC AND I EYE DON'T KNOW.
WE DO HAVE SUCH AN UP-AND-DOWN
RELATIONSHIP, BROTHER-SISTER,
BOYFRIEND-GIRLFRIEND WEIRD KIND
OF THING.
STILL, PART OF ME IS GLAD HE'S
NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT BECAUSE I
SAW A DIFFERENT SIDE OF HIM THEY
HAVEN'T SEEN IN THIS GAME.
AND I LIKED IT.
I LIKED IT A LOT.
JUST BE PATIENT.
TRUST ME.
>> WELL YOU KNOW RIGHT NOW IT'S
LIKE-- IT'S EITHER YOU OR ALEC
TONIGHT, RIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU DESERVE TO BE
HERE MORE THAN ALEC.
BUT I THINK YOU'RE SCARY ON
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES.
THAT'S YET DECISION IS
PROBABLY--
>> OH, ME?
>> YEAH, COME ON, ALEC IS
USELESS.
>> YEAR, HE IS.
>> WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
HIM WINNING.
>> I WAS REAL CLOSE AGAIN TO
GETTING THE NECKLACE TODAY, AND
I COULD KICK MYSELF RIGHT NOW.
I NEEDED IT.
EVERYBODY KNOWS I NEED IT.
IT IS A BAD FEELING.
IT'S BURNING YESTERDAY, AND IT'S
BURNING AGAIN TODAY THAT THEY'RE
JUST LAYING UP OVER THERE.
AND Y'ALL ARE TAKING THEM TO THE
END?
YOU ALL COULD SEND A MESSAGE
JUST LIKE THAT.
TAKE ALEC OUT OR TAKE ME OUT BUT
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
EVENTUALLY TAKE EACH OTHER OUT.
>> I HAVE BEEN FEELING
COMPLETELY HELPLESS TO DO
ANYTHING AT THIS POINT, BUT I
JUST REALIZED, OH, MY GOD, I
COULD TOTALLY FLIP THE ENTIRE
GAME.
>> YOU MIGHT NOT WANT TO THINK
WHO YOU WANT TO GO TO THE THREE
WITH BUT YOU BETTER START
THINKING.
>> KEITH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'M SMARTER THAN I LOOK
SOMETIMES.
RIGHT NOW THE PLAN IS SPLIT
VOTES.
ME, JON, AND JACLYN ARE VOTING
FOR KEITH, BUT FIFLIP, AND KEITH
VOTES ALEC, ALEC WILL GO HOME
AND KEITH WILL BE HERE, BE LOYAL
TO ME, AND I CAN USE HIM TO
BLINDS SIDE JON.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO VOTE FOR
TONIGHT?
>> I GUESS I'LL VOTE FOR ALEC.
>> FIDO THIS AND BETRAY JON, IT
WILL BE MY BIGGEST MOVE YET.
THE ONLY SCARY THING FOR ME,
THEN, IS DEALING WITH EVERYTHING
WHEN I COME BACK TO CAMP BECAUSE
JON IS GOING TO BE REALLY
PISSED.
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT I'M THINK.
I VOTE ALEC TONIGHT INSTEAD OF
KEITH.
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYBODY.
KEITH IS GOOD ON IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES AND WOULD BE AGAINST
JON.
>> NATALIE WANTS TO MAKE BIG
MOVES AND I DO AS WELL, BUT I
DON'T KNOW IF I WANT TO GET RID
OF ALEC RIGHT NOW.
IT'S A HUGE RISK BECAUSE JON
COULD FREAK OUT AND TURN ON US
IN A HEARTBEAT.
ALEC WILL DO WHATEVER WE SAY
AFTER KEITH'S GONE.
>> THE THING SI DON'T KNOW IF
IT'S WORTH IT ME GETTING IN
TROUBLE WITH MY ALLIANCE, SO I'M
GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE A
DECISION, I GUESS, TONIGHT.
ULTIMATELY, IT'S JUST DECIDING
IF I HAVE THE BALLS OR NOT UPON
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JOSH.
JEREMY.
WES.
AND REED VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, MISSY, BIG VOTE TONIGHT.
BECAUSE IF WE GO ON THE
ASSUMPTION THAT WE STILL HAVE
THIS ALLIANCE OF FIVE, YOU AND
BAYLOR, JON AND JACLYN, AND
NATALIE, AND WE HAVE THESE TWO
OUTSIDERS LEFT, KEITH AND ALEC.
FAIR ASSUMPTION?
FAIR ASSUMPTION.
>> Jeff: SO REALLY IT COMES
DOWN TO NOT ONLY WHO YOU VOTE
OUT BUT EQUALLY IMPORTANT WHO
YOU KEEP AROUND.
>> YEAH.
I THINK WE'RE LOOKING AT WHO IS
THE BEST AT CHALLENGES.
WHO WOULD BE HARDER TO BEAT.
>> Jeff: JON, DO YOU AGREE
WITH THAT, THAT IT'S REALLY
ABOUT WHO'S STRONG AT
CHALLENGES?
>> RIGHT NOW, YEAH, I THINK
THAT'S REALLY WHAT IT'S COMING
DOWN TO AT THIS POINT.
>> Jeff: SO IF THAT STRATEGY
COMES OUT TO PLAY, KEITH, THEN
YOU WOULD BE THE OBVIOUS TARGET
BECAUSE YOU'VE HAD A LOT OF
SUCCESS IN CHALLENGES.
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW, I'VE WON A
COUPLE OF IMMUNITY DEALS.
BUT I'M REALLY NOT GOOD IN SOME
OTHER STUFF, TOO.
SO IT'S A LOT TO THINK ABOUT.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, AM I MISSING
SOMETHING?
OR IS THIS JUST THE WAY THIS
GROUP IS GOING, THAT WE JUST
DON'T WANT ANYONE TO BEAT US?
>> UM, IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
BUT I WOULD SAY IF SOMEBODY'S
INTIMING IN CHALLENGES, THEN,
YEAH, THAT'S SCARY.
BUT I THINK THERE IS A LOT MORE
THAT GOES UNDER IT.
>> Jeff: SO WHOEVER SURVIVES
TONIGHT, FINDS THEMSELVES IN AN
INTERESTING SITUATION BECAUSE
HAVING A LOVED ONE IS NOT
NECESSARILY--
>> AAHH!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> IT'S A RAT!
SPHWHRU WOULD EAT THAT RAT?
>> I MEAN, THAT'S HOW HUNGRY I
AM, YEAH.
HONESTLY, AFTER EXILE ISLAND I
WOULD EAT THAT RAT WITHOUT A
HESITATION.
>> Jeff: JON, SEEING A RAT
SCURRY ACROSS TRIBAL COUNCIL
BRINGS IT ALL HOME TO WHAT'S
HAPPENING OUT HERE.
AND THAT IS YOU GUYS ARE LIVING
IN THE JUNGLE WITH NOTHING.
TRY TO PUT THIS IN PERSPECTIVE
FOR ME.
>> I ACTUALLY THINK BACK JUST TO
THIS MOST RECENT REWARD.
IT MIGHT SEEM LIKE THE SMALLEST
THING, BUT IT BROUGHT OUT A
TRAY, AND THERE WAS AN ACTUAL
WINE GLASS ON IT.
I'M A HUGE WINE FAN.
THAT'S BECAUSE MY DAD INTRODUCED
ME TO WINE, AND HE'S DYING OF
BRAIN CANCER RIGHT NOW, AND, YOU
KNOW, BEING OUT HERE JUST
REMINDS YOU WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
AND WHEN I WON THIS IMMUNITY
TODAY, I TEARED UP, BECAUSE I
KNOW THAT THIS IS ONE OF THOSE
MOMENTS THAT MY DAD IS GOING TO
BE ABLE TO SAY TO ME, "SON, I'M
PROUD OF YOU FOR THAT."
AND I DON'T HAVE VERY MANY OF
THOSE MOMENTS LEFT WITH HIM.
>> Jeff: WHEN YOU HEAR YOUR
DAD SAY THE WORDS "SON, I'M
PROUD OF YOU," WHAT IS THE
FEELING INSIDE?
>> I THINK THE BIGGEST THING
THAT COMES TO MIND IS REGRET.
BECAUSE MY DAD AND I REALLY ONLY
STARTED TO BOND A LOT THE PAST
TWO OR THREE YEARS.
AND I CAN ADD SO MUCH MORE TIME
AND COULD HAVE BUILT SO MUCH
MORE OF A RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM,
AND I LOOK BACK AT ALL THE YEARS
THAT I WAS STUBBORN AND THAT I
WOULDN'T LET HIM IN, THAT I-- I
REGRET IT EVERY DAY.
I REGRET SO MUCH OF IT.
>> Jeff: KEITH, YOU'RE A DAD.
YOUR SON IS SITTING RIGHT OVER
THERE ON THE JURY.
THIS GAME IS COMPLICATED.
BECAUSE ON ONE HAND, THIS IS A
VERY PERSONAL SHARING THAT JON
IS DOING.
AND YET, THERE'S THIS CRAZY
GAME.
AND IT'S ONLY A GAME.
BUT YOU CAN'T HELP BUT THINK,
MAN, COULD HIS TRAGEDY WORK
AGAINST ME IN THIS GAME?
AND IS THAT FAIR?
>> I-- I GUESS IT'S ALL FAIR ON
"SURVIVOR," BUT I HOPE THEM FOUR
OVER THERE ARE SHARPER THAN
THAT.
I'M GOING TO BE OVER THERE
EVENTUALLY.
A LOT OF US ARE.
AND I HOPE WE'RE SHARPER THAN
THAT TO SEE THROUGH SOME OF THIS
STUFF.
>> Jeff: SO, KEITH, IF YOU'RE
THE TARGET, AND YOU KNOW THAT,
WHAT DO YOU CO?
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T LAY DOWN AND
DIE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, JEFF.
I'VE GOT A VOTE HERE.
IF WE WANT TO DO SOMETHING, USE
MY VOTE.
SEE WHO THEY THINK.
SEE IF THEY'LL TAKE ME UP ON IT.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, THIS IS WHY
TONIGHT'S VOTE IS SO CRITICAL.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL OPPORTUNITY FOR
SOMEBODY IN THIS FIVE TO MAKE A
GIANT MOVE AND SAY TO THE JURY,
"I CAME TO PLAY, AND I CAME TO
WIN."
>> YEAH, I FEEL LIKE NO MATTER
WHAT AT THE END OF THE DAY, I
KNOW EVERYBODY IS THINKING ABOUT
ONE THING, WHICH IS THEY WANT TO
WIN A MILLION BUCKS.
SO NO MATTER WHAT ALLIANCE WE'RE
IN, EVERYBODY IS LOOKING OUT FOR
THEMSELVES.
AND I KNOW IT'S COMING AND IT'S
SCARY, BUT TONIGHT I'M CONFIDENT
THAT, YOU KNOW, ALL OF US ARE ON
THE SAME PAGE, NO SURPRISES WHEN
IT COMES TO THE ALLIANCE OF
FIVE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
BAYLOR, YOU'RE UP.
>> SORRY, BROTHER.
IT'S EITHER YOU OR ME.
HAD TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE.
KEITH.
ALEC.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES KEITH, TWO VOTES ALEC.
THAT'S THREE VOTES KEITH.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES ALEC, THREE VOTES
KEITH, ONE VOTE LEFT.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ALEC.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ALEC, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: WELL, BASED ON THE
REACTIONS AFTER THE VOTE, THIS
TIGHT ALLIANCE OF FIVE MIGHT NOT
BE SO TIGHT.
KEITH, THAT IS GOOD NEWS FOR
YOU.
>> SURE IS.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> Jeff: NATALIE WON'T REST
UNTIL SHE GETS REREVENGE ON JON.
>> I WANT JON OUT BAD.
>> Jeff: BUT ONE MOMENT COULD
CHANGE THE FATE OF THE GAME.
>> YOU NEED AN X-RAY.
>> IT'S FRUSTRATING!
>> I WOULD DEFINITELY SAY MY
AMBITION I CLEARLY WASN'T GOOD
AT ANY OF THE CHALLENGES.
AND THE ODDS WERE AGAINST ME FOR
A LONG TIME IN THE GAME.
AND I JUST KEPT FIGHTING AND I'M
NOT COMPLETELY CONTENT BECAUSE I
WANTED TO GO FURTHER.
BUT I GAVE IT MY ALL.
I DIDN'T WIN, BUT AT LEAST I
BEAT DREW.
SO THAT COUNTS AS A WIN FOR ME.